- [Narrator] Back of your neck stand up
and please enjoy the ride.
(upbeat music)
(people scream in excitement)
Get the best deal on tickets
at KingsDominion.com.
Kings Dominion, it's amazing in here.
(piano keys)
- [Narrator] Get ready for clearance.
It's the Honda 4th of July sales event.
Accords on clearance, Civics on clearance,
CR-Vs and HR-Vs on clearance
even the third row Pilot is on clearance
with features on clearance,
safety on clearance
and selection on clearance
like the new Civic for just $189 a month
(car engine revs)
or get a new CR-V for just $259 a month.
Don't miss the Honda
4th of July sales event.
Did we mention it was clearance.
Going on now at your local Honda dealer.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Now, ABC7
News At Noon on your side.
- And we are wishing
you a happy 4th of July
as we come on the air at noon.
Millions all across the nation
are celebrating America.
So many events happening in our area,
they're happening right now.
The National Independence Day
Parade is just kicking off.
That happened just a short time ago
and for now, it looks like
the weather is cooperating
but we are bracing for some storms
and our Steve Rudin, he's got the timing
and he is tracking all of this for us.
Steve, happy 4th to you.
- Same to you Lindsey
and we are looking at
the greatest threat for
those stronger storms
or heavier downpours
later on this afternoon
into the early evening hours.
Looking downstream on the Potomac
from our camera atop The Watergate Hotel,
we are dry right now but
that is going to change
over the next several hours.
Do have a Flash Flood
Watch for the D.C Metro
including Montgomery
County, Fairfax, Arlington,
Alexandria, the District
and Prince George's
and also parts of Loudoun County
until eight o'clock tonight.
Here's StormWatch7's Satellite and Radar.
A few showers beginning to bubble up
just across North East
D.C over toward Brookland
moving off toward the North and East.
Nothing heavy right now but
as mentioned that will change
as we head through the next several hours.
Here's our FutureCast.
This is the high resolution model.
We're gonna stop it for you at two o'clock
and look at how quickly this model
has those storms popping up.
They don't move very fast.
Could bring heavy rains to the District,
Arlington and Alexandria four pm
and continue as we move into the
all important six o'clock,
seven o'clock hour.
If there's any good news here,
by eight o'clock tonight,
showers become more limited
and then the fireworks display
is set to begin at 21:07 should go on
at least according to this model here
although the cloud deck may be
a little bit on the low side.
Worth watching and we're
going to keep you updated.
Look at these temperatures.
88 degrees already at
Reagan National Airport.
That is just part of the story
with feels like temperatures
now in the middle 90s.
We have a heat emergency
posted for the District
that is done by the District government.
Cooling centers are open
for those who need them.
Coming up in a few
minutes, an updated look
at our FutureCast plus we're looking ahead
to the rest of the long holiday weekend.
Lindsey?
- All right Steve and
we do want to talk about that just
the weather is holding up
so far for that National
Independence Day Parade and
our Nathan Baca is there.
So Nathan, happy 4th of July to you.
Just how crowded is it right now?
- Well it's getting more crowded.
I'm gonna show you the
situation right here.
I'm gonna do some crowd surfing over here.
So right now, I'm on
seventh approaching Constitution Avenue.
They are telling everybody
to move back from the street.
People wanna crowd onto the street.
In fact, I'm happening to kind
of move around some folks.
Hey, how's it going, happy
4th of July everyone.
So, this is what's going on right now.
Just to give you context,
here's the National Archives over here
(crowd of people cheer)
and you see some people here
celebrating 4th of July.
Where you guys visiting from?
Anybody?
- Atlanta.
- Washington D.C.
- Oh good you guys are local, excellent.
Well we, just to give
you some context again,
police are telling people to stay on back.
That right there is the Parade
and I'm gonna show you some
of the floats on down the way.
We've been noticing some bands.
People have been coming
here to hear those bands.
In fact, this is what some
people that were visiting,
not only from Alexandria
for the first time
but also from Georgia had to say.
- The reason why we're
out here is to celebrate
the independence from Great Britain.
Also our nation over the
last 243 years really
and then, to be amongst patriots.
- I don't see any controversy.
Like I see everybody
really coming together
and I'm just like, it makes me happy
cause we're not seeing anything
so vulgar, anything ugly,
it just makes me happy that
everybody's here together
to celebrate such a great day.
(marching band plays in background)
- All right now I talked
about one of those bands.
You see one of those bands right there.
That is what she was coming to hear
and there are plenty more bands
and plenty more floats coming on by.
So again, the situation here,
we do have a lot more, I'll say,
a lot more political signs,
a lot more political hats
and advertisements that
typically you would see
on a 4th of July parade
but a lot of folks are here,
just coming in from all around the country
hoping to just get a good party
and a good old D.C parade.
Reporting live from
Constitution and Seventh,
Nathan Baca, ABC7 News.
- All right Nathan, enjoy it down there
and that is just one of many
parades going on in our area.
The streets of Arlington,
it was packed there for
the annual Barcroft Parade.
(crowd cheers)
and this evening President Trump,
he is going to do his Salute to America
with an independence
extravaganza featuring tanks,
military flyovers and a
speech at The Lincoln Memorial
but some say the President
is politicizing a national holiday.
Mona Kosar Abdi has the very latest.
- [Mona] It will be "the
show of a lifetime",
President Trump has promised on Twitter
ahead of his extravagant
4th of July celebration.
(band plays)
A costly production,
Trump has also promised
will be worth the expense.
An array of military hardware on display
at The Lincoln Memorial including tanks
that have already been ushered in.
The Salute to America
spectacle will also include
multiple military flyovers
and an extended fireworks show
topped off with a speech
from the Commander and Chief himself.
- We're gonna have planes going overhead.
The best fighter jets in the
world and other planes too.
- [Mona] But the event is setting off
more than pyrotechnic devices.
It's also sparking backlash from critics
who accused the President of
staging a glorified campaign
rally and turning the celebration
into a partisan event.
The event is free but The White
House has given VIP tickets
to Republican National
Committee and top donors.
Congressman and 2020 Democratic
Presidential candidate Seth Moulton,
calling Trump's celebration
quote "Unamerican".
- It reminds me of the Soviet Union.
It's unpatriotic because
that's, militarism is not what
American patriotism is about.
- As for the price tag,
neither the Administration
nor the Pentagon
has disclosed what the
cost will be to taxpayers
but ABC News has learned
the National Park Service
is reportedly diverting
2.5 million dollars
from improvement projects.
President Trump adding overnight,
the fireworks have been
donated and the cost will quote
"be very little compared
to what it is worth"
and the $750000 worth of
fireworks were donated
by an Ohio company that lobbied
the President last month
to hold off on new tariffs on China.
The President announced he would do so
the same day he announced the donation.
Mona Kosar Abdi, ABC News, Washington.
- Security will be tight downtown today
and tonight for Independence
Day celebrations
and for President Trump's
Salute to America.
Each event has strict guidelines
on what you can bring and what you cannot.
The priority is safety.
No weapons, no alcohol,
not even drones or balloons are allowed
and for the Salute to America,
no backpacks, no large
purses, coolers or Tablets.
For a complete list, you can head over
to our website, WJLA.com
and you can find everything that you need
to know for today all in one list
whether you're heading to
events, wanting to avoid the city
or watching fireworks
in your neighborhood,
it is all on our free ABC7 News app.
(fireworks bursting)
we have a reminder this
Independence Day that fireworks
are not toys and they
need to be used properly.
The Consumer Products Safety Commission,
they always do these demonstrations
on the National Mall.
This is what they did last week.
They like to do these demonstrations
to show just how quickly
things can go wrong
when fireworks are not handled properly.
New data reveals that
emergency rooms across the US
treated more than nine thousand
fireworks related injuries last year.
More than half of those injuries
involving young children
were caused by Sparklers.
Happening right now, the
103th Annual Nathan's Hot Dog
Eating Contest is going on
in Coney Island, New York
and 11 time champ Joey Chestnut
looks like he might make history again.
He set a world record last year,
he ate 74 hot dogs in 10 minutes.
We are monitoring that and of course,
we will have some video for you later.
Coming up next at noon,
it's probably the largest
display of stars and stripes
that you'll see this holiday.
Find out where this is plus
(band plays)
celebrating America,
we have got a lot more
on the events happening
here and around the nation.
(band plays)
- [Narrator] Why do you
need the ABC7 News app?
To get instantly breaking news,
severe weather and traffic alerts.
Just download our app.
Go to settings.
Select push notifications.
Voila, it's that easy.
ABC7 News app, get it now.
- [Narrator] Hurry in now
to Value City Furniture
for the 4th of July sale
and save 10 to 30% off store wide
or enjoy 48 months special
financing on $9.99 or more
with payments starting
as low as $21 a month.
Only at Value City Furniture.
(somber music)
(dog squeals)
(baseball gets hit)
(door knocks)
- Bud, hello?
Hey, what's all this?
- Finally caught up and
ready for the next season.
Contour, find Prime Video.
- [Narrator] Now get Prime Video
and all your favorites on Contour TV.
From Cox.
- How do I get you Bob's discount
on such great quality furniture?
I build personal relationships
with my suppliers.
- Thanks for coming to
my kid's school play Bob.
- Stop lying Pinocchio, you're a bad boy.
(crowd laughs)
- I've been thinking,
I'll give you that deal
on extendable dining sets.
(violin plays)
- I just want to be a real boy.
(Bob sobs)
- [Crowd] Get Bob's discount.
- [Narrator] Only at
Bob's Discount Furniture.
- [Narrator] How do you
celebrate the 4th of July?
Show us with a picture.
Just upload your best shots
using our ABC7 News app.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Now at Value City Furniture,
shop our dream mattress studio
during the 4th of July sale
and save 30% off this Dream
Plus Queen Mattress Set
just $489 or enjoy 48
months special financing.
Only at Value City Furniture.
- [Narrator] ABC7's on
your side this capital 4th
with live coverage of the fireworks,
the President and the protests.
All day on ABC7,
WJLA 24/7 News
and wherever you go, streaming
on the ABC7 News app.
- The Justice Department
is hitting reverse
on its course over the
Census' citizenship question.
President Trump tweeted that
the Department of Commerce
and DoJ are working hard on this holiday
to keep that question.
As Trevor Ault reports,
our judges ordered the
Administration to resolve
the conflict by tomorrow.
- [Trevor] A week removed
from a Supreme Court decision
blocking the Administration from adding
a citizenship question to the 2020 Census,
President Trump still
defiant tweeting that
the Department of Commerce
and the Department of Justice
are working very hard on
this even on the 4th of July.
That message contradicting
the Justice Department's
announcement that Census
forms were being printed
without the question
"Are you a US citizen?".
- I think it's very important to find out
if somebody's a citizen
as opposed to an illegal.
- [Trevor] While the
President is insistent,
the fight for the citizenship
question is ongoing,
his comments have sparked confusion.
A Maryland Federal Judge
convened a conference call
Wednesday after she saw the
President's tweet saying
reports the question had
been dropped were fake.
On the call, Department of Justice lawyers
couldn't explain the President's rederick.
One lawyer saying quote
"the tweet this morning
was the first I had heard
of the President's position on this issue.
I do not have a deeper
understanding of what that means
at this juncture other than
what the President has tweeted".
The Justice Department did admit
the President contradicted them but said
they have now been
instructed to explore whether
there's a path forward
consistent with the Supreme Court
to allow the citizenship question.
The Trump administration
had previously argued
they needed the Census question
to better enforce the Voting Rights Act
but Chief Justice John Roberts shot down
that line of thinking
calling it contrived.
- The Court ruled that the
citizenship question was not
about whatever cockamamie
reason Donal Trump gave for it.
- While the Department of
Justice is following the
President's instructions,
they are running low on time.
They only have until tomorrow
to explain to the courts
how they plan to comply with
the Supreme Court's ruling.
Trevor Ault, ABC News, Washington.
- We have an update following
Monday's violent protests in Hong Kong.
Hundreds of protestors wreaked havoc
inside the city's legislative building
and four of them are now
talking about why they did it.
They tell the associated press that
the refusal of city leaders
to listen to their demands
drove them to desperation
and they say that they concluded
peaceful demonstrations
were pointless after the
failure of Hong Kong's
pro-democracy umbrella movement in 2014.
Pretty sure a lot of you might have been
freaking out a little bit
after realizing your Instagram,
your Facebook, WhatsApp
accounts were not working
the way there supposed to yesterday.
Well those issues have been resolved.
Users on the social
media platforms say that
they were having trouble
uploading or sending images.
There's no word yet on what
may have caused that issue.
Team USA now knows who they will be facing
in the World Cup final on Sunday.
It will be the Netherlands.
They were able to knock out Sweden
with a goal in the 99th minute
to punch their ticket to the final.
The good news for team USA,
co-captain Megan Rapinoe says that
she will be ready to go on Sunday
after missing the
semi-finals against England.
It's the largest flying display
of the stars and stripes in the nation.
The PNC American Flag balloon was inflated
this morning in Ridgefield, New Jersey
all in celebration of Independence Day.
That hot air balloon is five stories tall.
A pilot from Pennsylvania created it
after the attacks on 9/11.
The balloon is flown in
the New York City area
every year since then.
That's ginormous.
- Yeah, really big.
- Yeah
- All right--
- and you have to have
perfect weather for that too.
- For them, yes.
- Yeah.
- For today, not gonna want
to fly a hot air balloon.
So a lot to talk about moving
through the afternoon hours.
Crowds are beginning to build.
Heat emergency for the
District so stay hydrated
and the best news of
all, not everyone has AC
so cooling centers are
now open in the District.
So, good news there.
Do want to show you this time lapse
and this is our Skylapse7
for you showing Northwest D.C
and you can see,
actually the clouds
beginning to move on in.
These clouds will eventually produce
some heavier amounts of rain
as we move through the afternoon hours
and that's why we have a Flash Flood Watch
for parts of the area.
Live view right now, there are the clouds.
We are going to keep clouds in place.
Tidal Basin, looking quiet for right now
but we know those crowds are
definitely going to build
and then our camera atop the Watergate,
looking good right now although
it is on the hot and humid side.
88 degrees at Reagan National this hour.
88 in Leesberg.
85 degrees in Warrenton.
85 in Fredericksburg.
Do want to show you these
feels like temperatures.
Well into the middle to upper 90s
inside and around the Beltway.
Already feels like 104
degrees over Annapolis.
StormWatch7 Satellite and Radar does show
a few showers developing
North of Montgomery County
with some heavier downpours
inside the Capital Beltway.
Head off to the Cheltenham area,
over toward Laurel and Bowie,
that's where you're looking
at a few showers right now
but the showers and heavier
downpours are going to become
more prolific moving
through the afternoon hours.
Here's the latest for you
on the Flash Flood Watch
for the District, Arlington, Alexandria,
also Fairfax and Prince
William, parts of Loudoun,
Montgomery and Prince George's County.
As until eight o'clock tonight,
the all important FutureCast,
this is our high resolution model,
look at the heavy rain forecast
at two o'clock this afternoon.
Montgomery County and at Prince
George's over toward Andrews
and as we head through
the three o'clock hour,
once again the potential for
torrential downpours at the
District over toward North
East and upper North West D.C
and then we'll do it all over again
for the five o'clock and six o'clock hour
before things start to
settle down just a little bit
but some of these slow moving storms
capable of producing upwards
of two inches of rain
over a relatively short period of time
and by eleven o'clock tonight,
a little bit of patchy fog
but most of the storms are out of here.
Here's your 4th of July outlook
as we move through this afternoon.
Stay weather alert, temperatures
will be in the lower 90s.
Feels like temperatures
even hotter than that
with feels like temperatures
upper 90s to near 100 degrees.
Now waking up tomorrow morning,
it's hot and it's soupy once again.
Temperatures that will be in the 70s.
Highs tomorrow will eventually make it
into the upper 80s to around 90 degrees.
Unsettled again tomorrow
so grab the umbrella as you head outdoors.
Always download your
StormWatch7 Weather app
or at least have it ready to go.
It's gonna come in great
use later on this afternoon
especially if you're going
to find that perfect place
to watch the fireworks,
not only at the National
Mall but throughout the area.
Here's your seven day outlook Lindsey
and we have temperatures at
or above 90 degrees tomorrow
and Saturday and then a
little bit of a cool down
but to pinpoint exactly who's going to see
the heaviest of the rain, our
models do a pretty good job
in showing that over the
District and Arlington
and Alexandria, moving
through early to mid afternoon
into the early evening hours,
fingers crossed 21:07 tonight
we'll get all this out of here
but my other concern is a low cloud deck.
- Okay.
- Two years ago,
we had the fireworks.
- Right.
- Would of been beautiful
but when they shot up,
they disappeared and all
you saw were flashes.
So,
- Right.
- Could happen again this year.
- All right, so hopefully,
I'm gonna be an optimist here
- Yes.
- And say, fingers crossed,
hopefully all will go according
- I hope so.
- To our plan.
- We'll have a new update coming in.
- All right sounds good Steve, thank you.
Up next at noon, seven is on your side
with a health alert about sunscreen.
For all of you headed to
the beach this 4th of July,
are your kids applying it properly?
Up next, we are experimenting
to see if it's done the right way.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] There's a lot to smile about
in every Volkswagen.
Right now, you can lease a value packed
2019 Tiguan S for just $199 a month,
now with the people first warranty.
- [Narrator] It's the
final lap of Sheehy 8000.
Race in for special 4th
of July savings now.
Get up to 125% of KBB
value for your trade.
Plus we're donating to the
American Heart Association.
♪ It's easy at Sheehy ♪
♪ Sheehy.com ♪
- [Narrator] Marlo
Furniture's July 4th sale.
Time to declare your independence
from boring furniture.
With 60% savings on every
living room, every dining room,
every bedroom, 60% savings
plus free delivery
plus up to 60 months
zero interest financing
plus when you buy a mattress at Marlo,
we'll donate one to a
homeless veteran shelter.
Marlo Furniture's July 4th sale.
Upgrade your home, help
a homeless veteran.
Now that's worth celebrating.
- [Narrator] How do you
celebrate the 4th of July?
Show us with a picture.
Just upload your best shots
using our ABC7 News app.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] When someone's on your side,
you feel empowered.
That's why seven on your side is here
to help you fight back when
you're taken advantage of
and to give you information
to make the right
decisions for your family.
ABC7 News, on your side.
- [Narrator] It's Price Busters
Furniture's huge 4th of July
sale with Doorbusters
recliners $168, chairs $49,
bar and stools $78,
mattresses start at $49 save now.
Get it now and pay later
with no money down period
plus free delivery.
Price Busters Furniture, get there now.
- [Narrator] It's the final
lap of the Sheehy 8000.
Race in for special 4th
of July savings now.
Get your best price fast
and upfront with EasyPrice
plus we're donating to the
American Heart Association.
♪ It's easy at Sheehy ♪
♪ Sheehy.com ♪
- We are back now with a health alert.
As families head to the
beach this Independence Day,
we have got another reminder
of how important sunscreen is.
So parents, if you don't remind your kids,
odds are they may not
be putting it on at all
and when they do, are
they applying enough?
Becky Worley has the eye-opening
sunscreen experiment.
(upbeat music)
- [Becky] You know how
kids feel about sunscreen?
They hate it.
- I don't want sunscreen on.
I don't need it.
- I get annoyed.
- Sunscreen's icky.
- It's quite annoying.
- [Becky] But parents know it's a must.
The American Academy of Dermatology says
even one blistering childhood sunburn
is a contributor to
later life skin cancer.
So while the CDC says
children of all skin tones
should wear sunscreen regularly,
past research shows nearly
four in 10 kids don't.
Why?
Well I submit this
reenactment from my daughter.
- Put on sunscreen Emmy.
No I don't wanna put on sunscreen.
- It's a battle.
That's what I get.
(squeals in anguish)
Mom, stop.
But Holly Thaggard, a former
elementary school teacher
and founder of her own
sunscreen company, Supergoop!
says there is an alternative.
- If you're old enough to brush your teeth
and wash your hands,
you're old enough to
do your own sunscreen.
- Really?
Okay, let's try.
We're using a special camera
fitted with a UV Sensor.
When sunscreen goes on,
it shows up as black and
highlights any missed spots.
We start with seven to nine year olds
to see if their application is thorough.
The kids put it on then we
review what they missed.
- As each of these children
apply, none of them hit the ears
and the ears are actually
very vulnerable to sun damage.
- [Becky] Another frequent miss.
- [Holly] Children forget to apply it
right on into the hairline.
- [Becky] And something all the
younger kids struggled with,
not using enough sunscreen.
- Aw oh.
- When I come over here, what do you see?
- Uh, I missed a lot of spots.
(Becky laughs)
- [Becky] Holly says the
younger kids are afraid
of getting sunscreen
in their mouth or eyes.
- We're missing a few critical spots
right around the eye
area which is often where
sun damage is first detected from an aging
and a skin cancer perspective.
- [Becky] And a study showed kids using
just one quarter of the
amount of sunscreen needed
to get the protection
listed on the bottle.
Moving up to the older group,
the 11 to 12 year olds
were much more consistent.
Devin used a lot of
sunscreen and so did Gus,
also an 11 year old who
seemed to get the why.
- I feel like I try to
avoid it but I shouldn't
cause I know that having a
grandpa who had skin cancer,
so I shouldn't get it,
try to prevent that.
That's a lot isn't it?
- [Becky] But Holly says
he's doing it right.
- Use enough to where you're
applying it so that you can see
it on your skin and then rub
it in until you can't see it.
- [Becky] All the kids
said they learned a lot
and the takeaway, start them young
but kids 10 and under
need a lot of coaching
to get adequate protection.
- I always like the spray stuff.
Adults don't like it that much either.
All right now in our area, our weather,
we are on alert here, not rain just yet
but we are expecting some showers
at some point this afternoon.
Steve's gonna be back timing
it all for you after the break.
- We'll buy your house as
is and handle all repairs.
Get to life's next step with peace of mind
and cash in your pocket.
♪ Express Home Buyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
- Hello, I'm Mike Lindell,
inventor of MyPillow.
Thanks to your support,
you've helped make MyPillow
become one of the fastest
growing companies in America.
Over the last 12 years,
you've helped MyPillow
create thousands of jobs
right here in the USA.
Every MyPillow is made with
passion here in my home state
of Minnesota to ensure you get
the best sleep of your life.
- One of the things that I
really like about MyPillow
is the support.
It gives my neck a little hug.
- I've never slept better in my life.
What's better than a great night's sleep.
- Sleep is one of the most
important things to your health
and MyPillow is one of the most important
things to your sleep.
Call or go online now.
Take advantage of my two pack special.
Use the promo code and get
two MyPillows for just $69.98.
That's only $34.99 a pillow.
Call or go online now.
I tried every pillow
from expensive down
pillows that just went flat
to fiber filled pillows
that rebound every time
you move your head.
I even tried those memory
foam pillows and the curve
did not match my neck and it
probably won't match yours.
That's why I invented MyPillow.
My patented fill adjust to
your exact individual needs
and helps keep your neck
supported and aligned.
- When I got myPillow,
I'm asleep almost immediately.
I stay asleep at night and I wake up
more well rested in the morning.
- [Narrator] MyPillow lasts 10 years,
is machine washable and dryable
and comes with a 60 day
money back guarantee.
- I personally guarantee
MyPillow will be the most
comfortable pillow you'll
ever own or your money back.
Call or go online now.
Take advantage of my two pack special.
Use the promo code and get
two MyPillows for just $69.98.
That's only $34.99 a pillow.
Call or go online now.
With our 60 day money back guarantee,
you have nothing to lose.
- [All] Sleep well America.
♪ For the best night's sleep
in the whole wide world ♪
♪ Visit mypillow.com ♪
- The only thing that
I would do differently,
the only thing,
I should of called
Express Homebuyers sooner.
♪ Express Homebuyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
- All right welcome back.
We're talking about the weather
and it's the rain that we're
really keeping our eye on.
- Yeah and slow moving clusters of
wet weather that could bring
some very heavy downpours.
That's why we have a Flash Flood Watch
for the areas that are shaded
in green and more important,
the District, Arlington, Alexandria,
so many people trying to
find that perfect place
to find the fireworks this week
or this week, this evening.
This is what we expect
in terms of this evening.
We're going to call for
temperatures that are going to be
on the hot side and then by
two o'clock this afternoon,
look how the areas of
yellows and oranges of red
really begin to pop up on the screen.
Three o'clock and I'm gonna
stop this at four o'clock,
five o'clock, a little bit
of a lull but keep in mind,
this is just a computer simulation.
So these may be off, four, five miles.
In the big picture, that's not a lot
but it could make a
huge difference whether
it's over the District or
whether it's in Fauquier County
or whether it's in
Northern Montgomery County.
So everyone has a very
good chance of heavy rain
moving through the afternoon
into the evening hour.
- So, is everyone going
to be affected or possibly
just some people we don't
exactly know where just yet.
- We don't know exactly where.
- Okay.
- But pretty much everyone.
- All right.
- At this point.
- Thanks Steve.
- I wish I had better news.
(chuckles)
- We're gonna keep
tracking it for you though
and of course we have the app as well
so you can watch the
radar along with Steve
and we'll be back right after this.
(band plays)
- Hey, did you hear the big news?
- [Narrator] Huge Koons
July 4th savings are here
on thousands of new Koons Toyotas,
Fords, Chevys, Jeeps and more.
- [All] The biggest July 4th savings ever.
- [Narrator] Get started
now online at koons.com.
- But wait there's more.
- [Narrator] You might take
something for your heart,
your joints
or your digestion.
So why wouldn't you take something
for the most important part of you,
your brain.
With an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish,
Prevagen has been shown in clinical trials
to improve short term memory.
(upbeat music)
Prevagen, healthier brain, better life.
- This is Fred.
He's dancing like nobody's watching
and because all of the devices
on Fred's Wi-Fi network
are protected with Xfinity xFi,
literally nobody's watching
except the millions of you of course.
- Wait, millions of people are watching?
- Yeah, we're making a commercial.
- [Narrator] If it's
connected, it's protected
with Xfinity xFi.
Now that's simple, easy, awesome.
Get started with Xfinity for
$79.99 a month for two years
plus add xFi advantage for
enhanced network security.
Click, call or visit a store today.
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm Dan from MarketPro Homebuyers
and we want to buy your home.
Don't make repairs, don't pay commissions
and don't wait another day.
We'll get you the cash you need.
No agent fees, no closing costs.
We'll even help you
pack and move for free.
For a no obligation offer,
call 301-750-S-E-L-L.
That's 301-750-7355
or visit marketprohomebuyers.com.
We buy houses as is on your schedule.
Call today.
(knocks on glass)
- Hey, you still there?
There's more.
- [Narrator] On top of
huge Koons July 4th savings
on thousands of new Koons vehicles,
you'll get up to thousands
more for your trade
If your car is worth $8000,
- [All] Koons will give you ten.
- [Narrator] Get started
now online at koons.com.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Now, ABC7
News At Noon, on your side.
- Americans are ready to celebrate
the Independence Day
holiday in variety of ways.
From barbecues to fireworks
and meanwhile officials in
cities all across the nation
are taking precautions to keep
their large gatherings safe and secure.
Karin Caper is on Coney Island Boardwalk
in Brooklyn, New York.
That's where they're gearing up
for a very big day which
is already underway.
Karin?
- On the national level,
federal agencies say no
specific credible threats
against the holiday but law enforcement
will remain vigilant whether it's at
the major celebrations
like here in New York
or down in D.C or one of
the smaller celebrations
taking place across the country today.
Independence Day celebrations
set across the country
and AAA forecasts nearly
49 million Americans
making a getaway to celebrate.
- We see unemployment is low.
Americans have additional disposal income.
So, they're taking that
additional money and putting it
towards a trip with friends
and family this year.
- [Karin] In Washington, President Trump
will deliver a speech at The
Lincoln Memorial in addition to
the traditional fireworks
over the National Mall
and for the massive fireworks
display here in New York,
prime viewing spots will be
under the eye of the NYPD
with patrols in the air
and on the waterways.
Crowd safety measures will include
bag checks and thousands
of officers on duty.
- This is what the NYPD does.
We have so many large
events during the year.
We'll be ready, everybody come on down,
it's gonna be a great show.
- The National Retail
Federation estimates Americans
will spend $6.7 billion
on 4th of July barbecues.
Here at Coney Island,
they'll take things a few steps further.
At the corner of Surf
and Stillwell Avenues,
crowds will gather for the Annual
Nathans Hot Dog Eating Contest
watching competitors like
Gideon OG and Juliet Lee
who qualified at Washington's
Capital Barbecue Battle.
Contestants have 10 minutes
to down as many hot dogs
and buns as they can
and reigning men's champion Joey Chestnut
has won the competition
here 11 of the last 12 years
and last year, he set a
record with 74 hot dogs.
That might seem like a lot but
it is just a small fraction
of the 150 million hot dogs
Americans are expected to consume today.
At Brooklyn's Coney
Island, I'm Karin Caifa.
- And now to our weather.
Steve,
(band plays)
it's looking pretty
calm out there right now
but there are storms a brewing.
We can only hope that it
won't rain on anyone's parade
and we're listening to
that live music there
which is oh so nice
and of course we want them to be dry
when they're preforming.
- Yeah absolutely.
Unfortunately as we move
through the mid afternoon hours
into early evening, it's
gonna get wet around here.
To pinpoint exactly who's
going to see the heaviest rain,
best chances will be inside
and around the Capital Beltway.
That's where we already have
a Flash Flood Watch that's been posted
starting at one o'clock this afternoon
and extending until eight o'clock tonight.
StormWatch7 Satellite and Radar,
what's going on right now,
a few showers beginning to erupt
North and East of town,
nothing that is terribly heavy.
That heads to the Montgomery County,
Frederick County border
over toward Urbana,
North of Gaithersburg,
even a bit of thunder
and lightning right now.
Here's the latest for
you on our FutureCast
and this just updated for us.
Notice the showers,
thunderstorms begin to pop up
as we head through the two o'clock hour
becoming more numerous and
heavy as we head through
the four o'clock hour and then by six pm,
could be looking at a
heavier cell over Manassas,
over into Fairfax and
whether or not that moves
over the District or just pours itself out
is still yet to be determined.
Let's talk about temperatures right now.
88 degrees at Reagan National
but that's just part of the story.
We feel like the middle to upper 90s
to close to 100 degrees.
Coming up in a few minutes,
we'll show you FutureCast one more time
plus we're looking ahead
through the fireworks tonight
and then the upcoming weekend.
All that and much more coming up, Lindsey?
- Steve, thank you.
This 4th of July, ABC wants
to honor a true American hero.
A pilot who flew more than 400 missions
in three different wars.
It's a story that is very
close to Robin Roberts' heart
because of her own family legacy.
- On this July 4th, we
are giving the opportunity
to reflect on our rich history and those
who have served our country,
who protected and fought
for our freedom, the freedom
that we enjoy to this day.
No one better exemplifies this sentiment
than a true American patriot.
Bronze star, World War II
veteran, Colonel Charles McGee.
(upbeat music)
(crowd applauds)
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you for serving.
- [Robin] 30 years in the
Air Force, 409 missions
and 99 years young,
Colonel Charles McGee is an American hero.
Wherever he goes in his iconic
Tuskegee Airmen red blazer,
all eyes are on him.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for your service sir.
- Appreciate that.
- [Robin] The Colonel, one of
the first black Fighter pilots
who battled the enemy abroad
and segregation back home.
- The black American second class citizens
who digged dirt, built roads,
drive trucks, cook food
but do anything technical, impossible.
- [Robin] But the Tuskegee Airmen made
the seemingly impossible, possible
completing over 1200 combat
missions during World War II.
- You might say the Air
Force really led our country
in providing equal access and
equal opportunity for all.
- [Robin] On this day of
Independence, Colonel McGee
reminds us to set aside our differences
and stand united as a country.
- We are all American now.
Why they want to, for me say
oh you're African American.
What are you, German American?
And realize that it's
one of the big challenges
of today to recognize
all for who they are,
what they do and how they carry themselves
in supporting our country.
How's school?
- Oh good, good.
- Good?
- We're doing good.
- Keep it good.
You know why?
You're the future of the country.
And I love that and that's
what I try to pass on
young folks as they develop
their talents and find them.
Hopefully they put their finger
on something they enjoy doing.
You realize that you have to reach out
and share those experiences.
When folks ask how are things?
I just have to say life is a blessing.
- The Tuskegee Airmen also
known as the Red Tails
and I am an honorary member,
that's why I have my red blazer.
I'm also honored that I am the daughter
of a Tuskegee Airman,
Colonel Lawrence E. Roberts
and like Colonel McGee,
he shared his secret to
success with his children
and Colonel McGee's are
the four Ps he calls them.
Perceive, prepare, perform and persevere.
Sounds a lot like my daddy.
Many thanks to the friends of
the National World War II
Monument and the daughters
of the American Revolution for letting us
use their beautiful spaces.
We really did appreciate it.
Happy 4th of July.
(dinosaur roars)
- Everyone, watch out.
Larger than life dinosaurs
have arrived at the
Smithsonian's National Zoo.
(dinosaur roars)
Travel back millions of years
with ABC7 at Dino Summer
now through August 31st.
- [Narrator] StormWatch7,
seven strong on a mission.
- Knowing where the threat is.
- Knowing how it's going to impact you.
- That's makes all the difference.
- [Narrator] StormWatch7, seven strong
and always on your side.
- This does not look like a discount sofa.
- It's not, everything I sell
is quality furniture and
I give you a discount,
Bob's Discount.
- Interesting.
I'll remember this for as long as I live.
Bob, you look so young.
- Do you remember?
- It's not discount furniture,
it's quality furniture at a discount.
- [Bob] Bob's Discount.
- [Crowd] Get Bob's discount
- [Bob] Only at Bob's Discount Furniture.
- [Narrator] No matter your plans,
there's a Cox Internet plan for you.
Starting at $29.99 a
month for up to 10 megs.
Plus panoramic Wi-Fi blankets your home
with fast, reliable Internet.
Cox has fast one gig speeds everywhere.
Super fast speeds for those things
you just can't live without.
Get Internet starting
at just $29.99 a month
for up to 10 megs.
Call today to get the Internet
plan that fits your life.
Cox Internet.
- Here's your Buick sir.
- Actually that's my Buick.
- Your Buick doesn't have a roof rack.
- This is my Buick.
- How are we gonna fit
in your mom's Buick?
- Easy.
- I like that new Buick.
- Me too.
- I was actually talking about that Buick.
- I knew that.
- Did you?
- [Narrator] Buick's fresh new
line up is full of surprises.
During Buick's 4th of July sales event,
pay no interest for 76 months
on most 2019 Buick models.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Survive Metro's
Summer shutdown with ABC7 News.
Count on ABC7 on your side
coverage from start to finish
wherever you are to keep you on track.
- I want to thank you and
your team for getting word out
cause that's really made a big difference.
- [Narrator] ABC7 News, on your side.
- We are back now with
a 15 year old phenom
who continues to dominate
opponents twice her age
Ian Pannell is in Wimbledon and has,
or is at Wimbledon and has more
on Coco Gauff's latest win.
- [Ian] Overnight, this fairytale
got another incredible chapter.
(crowd cheers and applauds)
With poise and power beyond her years,
15 year old Cori Coco Gauff
sailed into the third round
of Wimbledon after dominating
an opponent twice her age.
- [Commentator] The newest
star shines a little brighter.
- [Ian] Coco's latest
victory coming just two days
after the American teen
sensation rocked the tennis world
with a first round victory
over her idol Venus Williams.
- [Commentator] It's a dream
debut for the 15 year old.
- [Ian] That win making
her an instant star
bringing the praise and
approval of some of the greats.
- Hey there she is.
How's everything?
- Good.
- Congratulations, great job.
- Thank you.
- When are you playing?
- Last on court two.
- Oh okay, play well.
- Thank you.
- Cheers, bye.
- You got that on camera?
(laughs)
I can lie and say it wasn't hard
but it was definitely hard to
reset all this buzz going on
and I was just telling myself if you want
more moments like that, you
got to continue to work hard
and continue to stay focused.
- [Ian] But reset she did, on Wednesday
defeating Slovakia's Magdalena Rybarikova.
(crowd cheers and applauds)
The packed house and her proud parents
on their feet in a rare ovation.
- [Commentator] And she
did it with such style.
- Everything has come together.
I am so proud of my daughter.
Watching her, the maturity
that she has developed
in this last week and a half, two weeks.
- Obviously she wants
to win the tournament
but regardless of the outcome, for me
we've already had a success
cause we've come here
and we've seen growth in her.
- [Ian] Coco now the
youngest woman to advance
to Wimbledon's third round since 1991
and she's not intimidated.
- I think I can beat anyone
who's across the court
and if I don't think I can win the match
then I won't even step on the court.
- She's on the top of her game
and you are on the top of yours today.
You are looking at the forecast
with a fine tooth comb.
- Absolutely and a lot to
talk about, hour by hour
as we move through the afternoon.
This right here is Skylapse7
and look at the boat
traffic on the Potomac.
Up and down, everyone's trying
to get from point A to point B.
This is what it looks like,
a live view for you right now
showing our skies are hazy
and cloudy, at least it's dry
inside the Capital Beltway.
Over toward Friendship
Heights and Chevy Chase,
clouds continue to build
and our next stop, the Tidal Basin,
traffic look at that,
doesn't look that bad
but a lot of roadways are
closed so be sure to check
with ABC7, WJLA.com for
the latest traffic maps.
88 degrees right now at Reagan National,
87 Manassas,
feels like temperatures
already at 100 in Leesburg,
feels like 96 degrees at
Reagan National Airport.
A heat emergency for the District.
That means cooling centers
are now open throughout the District.
So if you don't have AC or you
need a place to take a break,
that's where you need to go.
Heat index values throughout the afternoon
well into the 90s.
Some of these heavier
downpours will cool us down
but it's still gonna stay
really sticky out there
moving through this
afternoon into this evening.
StormWatch7 Satellite and Radar,
look at the showers,
the heavier rain already
beginning to blossom
North of Gaithersburg, up toward Urbana,
Barnesville, Damascus, all
looking at wet weather right now.
The same for Lanham,
nothing that is severe
but slow moving storms
capable of producing
very heavy rain over
a short period of time
and also the potential for
localized flash flooding.
Flash Flood Watch goes
into effect at one o'clock
this afternoon until
eight o'clock tonight.
All the areas that are shaded in green.
Here's our FutureCast.
I'm gonna stop this for you hour by hour
moving through this afternoon and evening.
Notice the wet weather,
develops two o'clock,
three o'clock, North and East of D.C.
The Eastern edge of the Capital Beltway.
Moving into the four o'clock hour,
a little bit of a lull
at least for the District
but then by five pm,
we could be looking at
heavier rains just off toward
the South at West of us.
The big question mark,
where will these storms set up exactly?
Will it be over the District?
Will it be over Fairfax?
It's anyone's guess at this point.
What I can recommend, if you're going out
to the National Mall,
take extreme caution,
make sure that you have
a secure place to go
should you find some of these
heavier downpours overhead.
If there's any good
news with this forecast,
moving into the nine o'clock hour,
heaviest of the rain begins to diminish
and the chances for the heavier
rain will begin to ease.
By 11 o'clock tonight, a
lot of folks going home,
things should begin to
improve just a little bit
although we may see a
little bit of patchy fog.
For this afternoon and into
the evening for the fireworks,
temperatures will be in the 80s.
Waking up early tomorrow morning,
temperatures are in the 70s once again,
very warm, very humid.
Highs tomorrow will make it into
the mid to upper 80s
to close to 90 degrees
and we are looking at yet another round
of wet weather through
the afternoon hours.
Seven day outlook from StormWatch7,
91 on Saturday, 87 degrees on Sunday,
we drop back down to the
80s come early next week.
Lindsey?
- All right Steve, thank you
and Seven is on your side
with a Summer holiday warning.
According to the CDC,
drowning is the leading cause
of unintentional deaths in
children ages one to four.
So before you head to
the pool or the beach
to celebrate the 4th, Gio
Benitez is taking a look
at how to keep your family safe.
(water splashes)
- [Gio] It looks like any
other Summer pool party.
Young people splashing in the water,
parents enjoying the barbecue
but somewhere in this pool,
five different swimmers
are about to simulate
that they're drowning
and we're wondering if these
moms and dads can spot them.
Drowning can happen in just seconds
and it's often difficult to spot.
It's happening to someone in
this public pool right now.
Can you spot it?
There she is.
(whistle blows)
Fortunately a lifeguard spots
her and makes the rescue.
But it's in residential pools
where lifeguards usually aren't present
that the majority of drownings take place.
Safety experts say part of the
reason, distracted parents.
Talking on their phones,
grilling, socializing
and supervising other children
with no water watcher,
a person with eyes on
the water at all times.
So we've invited this group
of parents to a pool party,
assigning them tasks like
running that grill and of course,
tending to their own young kids.
We've also added swimmers
splashing in the pool
but those swimmers are
actually trained lifeguards
and swim instructors from
Swim Jim's swim school
skilled in mimicking a drowning.
The parents know they're here
to learn about water safety
with some sort of demonstration
beginning in about an hour
but since drowning often happens
when you least expect it,
we begin right now.
With cameras rolling,
I watch from a garage
just next to the pool
observing some parents
checking the water but
mostly they're focused on
their assignments and the party
and after 30 minutes,
there we go, she went under,
our swim instructor Kelly
begins simulating a drowning,
struggling to keep her head above water,
arms clawing for the surface
and just like the real thing,
she barely makes a sound.
Meanwhile, our guests seem not to notice.
More than a minute goes by.
She's still struggling
and nobody's looking.
We're now looking at more
than two and a half minutes
and still nobody notices a thing.
After more than four minutes,
she simulates a worst case
scenario and stops moving.
Remember, she's a trained
professional and is just acting.
Josh from the American Red
Cross has been watching with us.
Four and a half minutes, still
no parent noticed anything.
- Right.
- Does that surprise you?
- It does not.
- [Gio] Kelly goes back to swimming
and we cue another swimmer
and another
and another,
all mimicking a drowning
but nobody steps in.
- We don't realize how
quickly these kind of things
can go from just a fun pool party
to an incident where someone needs help.
- So now, the kids are
gonna get out of the water.
They're gonna go get some snacks
and they're gonna leave someone behind
and that person is gonna start drowning.
After 30 seconds of purposeful struggling,
this dad spots her.
- You all right?
Huh?
- Within 36 seconds, he noticed.
- It's great that he noticed.
We hope that they would notice faster.
- He says in some cases,
swimmers can submerge in
just seconds making them
even more difficult to spot.
It's time to reveal our experiment.
Someone was drowning.
There were four drownings
that nobody spotted.
What's that make you think?
- My kids are on the
deck so I turned my back.
Doesn't mean there weren't
other kids in the pool though.
- I got thrown off by the age.
So I think we took for granted
that they all knew how to swim.
- For the man who spotted our victim,
it's too close to reality.
You were visibly shaking.
- Yeah.
- [Gio] Why were you so nervous?
- It's,
it did happen
to my child.
- [Gio] His daughter Valentina survived
but he says when she was just three,
she began drowning in a hot
tub, he was on the phone.
- I got a phone call and
I got distracted and she was in trouble.
So, that brought memories.
- Water safety experts
say one of the solutions
is a water watcher, somebody
standing next to the pool
free from distractions,
constantly scanning the water
for any signs of distress,
rotating every 15 minutes
to avoid losing focus.
We showed the parents what they missed.
This is that moment when
she's motionless in the water
and this seems to be
very emotional for you.
- They're all our kids.
What else do you say?
- [Narrator] At Cookology,
our goal is to inspire people
to connect over a great meal.
Our chefs teach hands-on cooking classes
to adults and kids everyday in
our safe commercial kitchens
in Dalston Center in Ballston Quarter.
Sign up today at CookologyOnline.com.
- I'm Kidd O'shea.
Check out Cooking With Kidd every Tuesday
as the area's top chefs and
foodies join me in the kitchen.
See what we're cooking
on ABC7 News at Four.
- [Narrator] Cooking with
Kidd is brought to you
by Ballston Quarter and Cookology.
- This is an important announcement.
Funeral costs are rising every year
costing thousands upon thousand of dollars
and more and more families
are shocked and unexpectedly
burdened with funeral costs
when a loved one dies.
You don't have to let that happen.
If you're a United States resident
between the ages of 40 and 85,
now is the time to call about
the Funeral Advantage Program.
Through the Funeral Advantage Program,
your family receives a
life insurance cash benefit
up to $20000 in the event of your death.
If you live in a qualifying state
and you're between age 40 and 85,
call now because you are eligible
for a free Funeral
Advantage Program offer.
Don't put it off.
Call the number on your
screen now to request
your Final Wishes organizer,
free without obligation.
The Final Wishes organizer will help make
many difficult decisions
easier and uncomplicated.
Don't delay.
When you call, we'll add
this second important
booklet absolutely free.
"The 9 Things Every Senior
Needs To Know About Funerals"
puts the facts on funeral
planning in plain language.
You may be surprised by what it reveals.
Call now.
Call 1-800-917-3700
to find out more about Funeral Advantage.
You have absolutely no risk or obligation.
1-800-917-3700.
Don't wait, call 1-800-917-3700 now.
- [Narrator] How do you
celebrate the 4th of July?
Show us with a picture.
Just upload your best shots
using our ABC7 News app.
(upbeat music)
- In today's Spotlight on Education,
we're taking a closer look at a program
designed to enrich students
and keep them plugged
into learning during the Summer months.
Kelly Lin is taking us to North West
for a look at the Summer
Discovery Program.
- [Teacher] Let's name them one by one.
- [Students] Mercury, Venus, Earth.
- [Kelly] A journey to space,
an encounter with heroes
and villains and the
execution of simple missions.
- In Simple Missions, we
are architects and engineers
and in Heroes and Villains,
we learn to draw and write our comics.
- [Kelly] Just a few of the
activities and themes offered
through the D.C public school's
Summer Discovery Program.
- The goal is to reduce Summer
learning loss and to give
our scholars enrichment
opportunities all Summer long.
- I'm learning how to draw and mythology.
- [Kelly] Learning that
comes at no charge.
- [Teacher] Could we survive in space?
- [Students] No.
- [Kelly] And is offered at eight campuses
across the city during the
months of June and July.
- For every scholar that's
in the Summer school program,
they also have a slot in
our after schools program.
So we're offering programming
from eight am to 5:30 pm.
- [Kelly] For nine year old Salway Brenin,
the STEM focused content allows her
to pursue some of her favorite activities.
- I like engineering and designing things.
- [Kelly] In the DCPS
Summer Discovery Program.
- [Teacher] And we're
gonna start here tomorrow.
(bell rings)
- [Kelly] At Garrison
Elementary in North West,
- [Teacher] High Five Space Cadets!
- [Kelly] Kelly Lin, ABC7 News.
- If you know someone in
education or a program
that Kelly should be
shining the spotlight on,
we wanna hear from you.
All you can do is go
to WJLA.com/OnYourSide
to send in your suggestions
and stick with us,
Steve's gonna be back with
a final check on your holiday
forecast after the break.
(upbeat music)
(band plays)
(car honks)
- I'm Kevin Goldberg.
If you've been injured in
an automobile accident,
don't sign a release
until you speak to us.
Call 1-800-JUSTICE for
a free case evaluation.
Goldberg Finnegan, protecting your rights.
- Are you looking for a hassle free,
simple way to sell your home as is.
It doesn't matter if you're
downsizing your home,
have fallen behind on
repairs or your mortgage.
Get an offer on your home
in as little as 10 minutes
with House Buyers of America.
We buy houses directly.
There's no middle-men, no commissions.
There's no need to deal
with real estate agents,
repairs, inspections and renovations.
Give us a call today.
We're A plus rated with
the Better Business Bureau.
House Buyers of America,
real estate made real easy.
- Today is a special day.
It's my son's 16th birthday.
So, we'll take it.
- Dad, are you serious?
You're getting me a Benz?
- What!
Oh no, no, no.
You're getting the old
car, I'm getting the Benz.
(laughs)
- [Narrator] Ready for your dream car?
AMKO's got it.
Visit for the best selection,
best prices and the financing you need.
- Don't wait for me, I'll be on a joyride.
- Man!
♪ The M, the K, the O, it's AMKO ♪
(knocks fridge)
- [Narrator] Appliance shopping
shouldn't be painful.
Come to Bray and Scarff
where factory trained appliance experts
give you the personal
attention you deserve
and get July 4th savings now
with exclusive double rebates
on select KitchenAid packages
plus this Maytag top load washer
with deep fill and power
wash for just $699.
Shop local at Bray and Scarff,
where it doesn't cost more to get more.
(somber music)
- [Narrator] You're a person
not a credit score
but sometimes your score gets in the way
of the things you want to do.
Personal consumer loans through NetCredit
help you borrow up to $10000
and you can check if you're
eligible on NetCredit.com
without affecting your credit score.
You may even be able to build
your credit history as you repay.
NetCredit, a more personal, personal loan.
Visit NetCredit.com today.
- If you've been injured in an
accident, call 1-800-JUSTICE
and we'll meet with you free
of charge to discuss your case.
You don't know if the
insurance company is being fair
until you talk to an attorney.
Goldberg Finnegan, protecting your rights.
- [All] Three, two, one, go!
(crowd cheers)
- The Nathans Hot Dog Eating Contest
is happening right now but
last night in our area,
two divisions competed in the
Palisades Pie Eating Contest.
There was a kids challenge
and then one for the adults.
It's so much cuter with the kids.
The twist is that this was
obviously hands free there.
Goodness.
- Wow, what a mess.
But a lot of fun.
- Wow.
- I think I can do better if
it was like chocolate cream
or coconut cream as
opposed to a fruit pie.
- I feel like the cherries
are easier to, you know.
- It's a mess
but a lot of fun.
- I don't know.
- All right so here we go
through the afternoon hours.
We are live now, almost one o'clock.
We have a Flash Flood Watch
that will go into effect
in about four minutes until
eight o'clock tonight.
Areas that are shaded in green.
Here's our FutureCast, two o'clock.
Notice East of D.C, heaviest
the downpours are on the way
and as we move through
the three o'clock hour,
the four o'clock hour, this
is our high resolution model.
It does keep the heaviest of the rain
at least according to this
model outside of the Beltway
however this could shift a
few miles and around here,
three, four, five, six miles
makes a big difference.
As we move into the seven
o'clock hour, eight o'clock hour,
things begin to improve for the fireworks.
So your 4th of July afternoon
and evening forecast looks like this.
It is hot, it is humid.
Temperatures well into the
upper 80s to near 90 to start.
Heavier downpours could bring
upwards of two inches of rain.
Localized flooding, even some
thunderstorms with gusty winds.
We're gonna keep you updated
all afternoon right here on ABC7
and on WJLA.com.
Bill will be in here, I'll join
him later on this afternoon.
- Have a really wonderful day.
Happy 4th of July and we'll
see you back here at four.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Stay ahead of the storms
with the StormWatch7 app.
Live radar, severe alerts,
lifestyle forecasts and more.
Download the StormWatch7 app,
always with you, always on your side.
- [Narrator] ABC7 News at six followed by
World News Tonight weeknights.
- Set your eyes on my latest game changer.
A world famous Bob-O-Pedic
Queen Mattress for only $299.
With all the quality and
comfort of its more expensive
cousins, it's really a
little gem of a mattress.
So that's what we called it.
The Bob-O-Pedic Gem.
- [Crowd] Get Bob's discount!
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm Dan from MarketPro Home Buyers
and we wanna buy your home.
- My husband and I were
faced with a decision
of what to do with my father's home.
The house required a lot of work.
That's when I found MarketPro Home Buyers.
Dan visited our home and within
minutes, he gave us a quote.
It was so easy.
Dan even helped pay to pack and move us.
MarketPro Home Buyers
truly helped my family
when we did not know what to do.
- [Dan] Call us today at 301-750-7355.
♪ Me-He-He ♪
- It's meant to be.
- Yeah.
♪ Ooh, Ooh, Ooh, Ooh, Ooh ♪
♪ I'm the only one of me ♪
♪ Baby that's the fun of me ♪
- [Narrator] It's your Me Time!
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
GMA at seven,
Live With Kelly and Ryan at nine,
Rachael at 10,
The View at 11
and Strahan and Sara at one.
♪ Me-He-He ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
- Yes!
♪ And I promise that nobody's
gonna love you like ♪
- [Narrator] Your Me Time! ABC7
(knocks fridge)
- [Narrator] Appliance shopping
shouldn't be painful.
Come to Bray and Scarff
where factory trained appliance experts
give you the personal
attention you deserve
and get July 4th savings now
like the lowest prices of the season
on the GE Profile packages
plus this GE french door
refrigerator, now $1999
in stainless, slate or black slate.
Shop local at Bray and Scarff