- The financial compensation they deserve.
If you've been hurt in a car accident,
been the victim of medical malpractice,
or been denied Social
Security disability benefits,
please let us help you too.
Call us at 301-589-2200
or visit us on the web at
GBLawyers.com.
Greenberg & Bederman,
call us, feel better.
- [Announcer] At PenFed Credit Union,
we believe in helping
our nation's defenders
secure their own home fronts.
Act now for the lowest rates
of the season on VA loans.
Visit penfed.org.
♪ PenFed's got great rates for everyone. ♪
- [Cecilia] Tonight, breaking news.
The verdict just in.
The decorated Navy SEAL
accused of murdering
a wounded prisoner in Iraq.
The stunning moment when
another SEAL team member
took responsibility for the killing.
What the jury has just decided.
Also breaking, the explosion
rocking an American neighborhood.
The blast destroying a home,
firefighters frantically
digging through rubble
looking for possible victims.
The man calling 911 saying
he's trapped under the debris.
The nail biter World Cup victory,
Team USA beating England,
their star player on the sidelines hurt.
So will she be there for the finals?
A scathing new government
report about life
inside those migrant detention centers.
Men kept for a week in
standing room only cells.
One manager calling the
scene "a ticking time bomb".
What Homeland Security is now saying.
Growing backlash over President Trump's
4th of July plans, tanks and fighter jets
headed to the National Mall.
The president accused
of turning the holiday
into a political rally.
The mystery over the sudden
death of Angels' pitcher
Tyler Skaggs, found dead in his hotel room
in the prime of his career.
What authorities and
the team revealed today.
And the shark scare off the coast,
a mother and her children in the water
with no idea what's lurking
just a few feet away.
- [Narrator] This is ABC World
News Tonight with David Muir.
- Good evening, and it's
great to have you with us
on this busy Tuesday night.
I'm Cecilia Vega in for David
and we begin with that bombshell verdict
in the war crimes trial
of a former Navy SEAL.
A military jury finding
Special Operations Chief
Edward Gallagher not guilty
of murdering a captured ISIS fighter.
Gallagher was convicted of a single crime,
taking a photo with the
body of a dead captive.
Gallagher was deployed
to Iraq in 2017 when
the incident took place,
his own platoon turning him in.
But then that stunning
turn during the trial.
A prosecution witness testifying that he,
not Gallagher, actually
killed the captive.
ABC's Clayton Sandell starts us off.
- [Clayton] Edward Gallagher's
attorneys celebrating tonight
on the steps of the courthouse after a
military jury found the
decorated Navy SEAL not guilty
of premeditated murder.
- Huge victory, huge
weight off the Gallaghers.
Huge victory for justice.
- [Clayton] The 19 year combat veteran
was accused of war crimes
during a 2017 tour in Iraq
including murdering this
teenage ISIS prisoner
seen wounded in this Iraqi TV video.
Fellow SEAL Corey Scott, granted immunity,
testified that he saw Gallagher, a medic,
stab that teen in the neck.
But in a shocking twist,
Scott testified that he,
not Gallagher, killed the
teen by plugging his airway
to prevent him from being
tortured by Iraqi forces,
saying "I knew he was
going to die anyway".
Gallagher's defense team
argued during the two week
trial that the case was
built on false accusations
from disgruntled sailors.
- This is not a murder, this is a mutiny.
This is a group of young,
disgruntled sailors
that didn't like being told
that they were cowards.
And so they decided to conspire
to take down the chief.
- And Clayton Sandell joins us now live.
Clayton, we know that Edward
Gallagher was convicted
of that one charge, posing for a picture
with the captive's dead body.
So, could he still face prison time?
- That's right, Cecilia.
Prosecutors showed those
pictures during the trial.
Defense attorneys argue that
the sentence for that crime
would be less than the
time he's already served.
So they believe Gallagher
will be going home tonight.
Cecilia?
- Clayton Sandell leading us
off this evening, thank you.
To our other top story tonight,
that massive explosion
rocking an entire neighborhood
in North Carolina.
This stunning image from above.
A hole where a home used to be.
First responders combing
through the rubble,
one man trapped underneath
using his cell phone
to call for help.
He was rescued along with
at least two other people,
but the urgent search for
other victims goes on.
Here's ABC's Steve Osunsami.
- [Witness] It is just jaw
dropping to see this scene.
- [Steve] Families
across this neighborhood
in an expensive suburb
of Charlotte say it felt
like an earthquake.
- [First Responder] The house
exploded and is now on fire,
also reporting insulation in the trees.
Unknown if anyone's inside.
- [Steve] From the sky you could see
the desperate search for survivors.
Firefighters trying to saw
through large piles of wood.
- [Witness] A natural gas sort of issue
or if it's something else,
but it is still burning.
- This is what's left of
this large home in Valentine.
For reasons that aren't clear
at this hour, it exploded.
- [First Responder] We do have contact
with one trapped on the phone right now.
We're trying to find the location of where
they're at in the rubble.
- [Steve] A man who was inside the home
was buried under all of this.
He had a phone nearby,
was able to call 911,
and lead firefighters directly to him.
Here he's being airlifted to the hospital.
- They were on the phone
talking to alarm at the time
and did provide their location
which assisted greatly in
locating and removing the patient.
- Authorities continue
to search for at least
one other possible victim tonight.
The blast also tore into
this home next door.
Two neighbors were treated
by medics at the scene.
This is difficult weather for
the firefighters to work in
with temperatures in the
90s, pushing 100 degrees,
more than 80 firefighters
were called into help.
Cecilia?
- Urgent search there,
okay Steve, thank you.
And from France tonight,
that nail biter victory
for team USA.
The women celebrating a
close game against England
in the World Cup semifinal.
They now head to the finals.
But today's win happened
without their star player,
so will she be there for the clincher?
ABC's Adrienne Bankert
is outside the stadium.
- [Sports Announcer] That was it, US wins.
- [Adrienne] Tonight,
victory, team USA now charging
straight for that World Cup
final after a two to one win
over England.
(cheering)
Tens of thousands of Americans
cheering in the stands
here in Lyon.
The epic matchup getting
off to a stunning start
with star Megan Rapinoe on the sidelines,
no warmup with the team.
It sparks worry about a possible injury.
At game time Christen
Press takes her place,
not missing a beat.
- [Sports Announcer] Right side cross.
Done, go!
(Cheering)
- [Adrienne] Even a goal
from England powerhouse
Ellen White couldn't stop
USA momentum for long.
- [Sports Announcer] Me,
drives it from white, goal!
England have tied it.
- [Adrienne] Then there was
Alex Morgan with this move
on her 30th birthday.
- [Sports Announcer]
Grand, setting it in there,
hey there, goal!
- [Adrienne] At home, fans
glued to their screens
from Brooklyn to Chicago to Los Angeles.
- [Sports Announcer] (mumbles) goal!
- [Adrienne] And just when
England thought it tied the game,
this call from the ref offsite, no goal.
- [Sports Announcer] Calling
the shot, safe by a minute.
- [Adrienne] True American
grit captured in this moment.
USA goalkeeper Alyssa Naeher diving
to block this penalty kick.
- To see them win and go
to the World Cup finals,
whoo, I am so energized.
(Adrienne laughing)
- It was quite a game, and
Adrienne Bankert was right there
for it all, she joins us
from outside the stadium
there in Lyon now.
Adrienne, all eyes on Megan Rapinoe.
Is she expected to play on Sunday?
- Yes, she is.
The team confirms it was a
minor strain in her hamstring
but she will be on the field
on Sunday for the final.
And again, even in her absence,
you can tell from tonight's performance,
team USA has quite the rich roster.
Cecilia?
- They sure do, okay, Adrienne, thank you.
Back here at home now a new
report is fueling fresh outrage
about conditions inside those
migrant detention centers.
The department of Homeland
Security's own inspector general
found families held in overcrowded
rooms in one Texas center
and standing room only for men at another.
One facility manager calling
the situation there "a ticking time bomb".
ABC's Will Carr reporting
again from the border tonight.
- [Will] Tonight we have
new images from inside
jam packed migrant holding
centers showing what the
government calls dangerous overcrowding.
One facility manager says
the situation is so dire
it's a "ticking time bomb".
The images are part of a Homeland
Security Inspector General
report just released today.
They found some adults wedged
into standing room only cells
for up to a week.
Others were held for up to
a month in these conditions.
You can see their hands
pressed against the windows.
They saw children with
no access to showers
and limited clothing.
In response, DHS says it
treats those in custody
"with the utmost dignity and respect",
adding, "the current migration
flow and the resulting
"humanitarian crisis
are rapidly overwhelming
"the ability of the federal
government to respond".
Today, hundreds took to the
streets in cities across
the country calling for
the centers to close.
From Austin--
- [Protestor] Don't be
silent, ICE is violent.
- [Crowd] Don't be silent, ICE is violent.
- [Will] To Miami.
- [Crowd] Close the camps now.
Close the camps now.
- [Will] And here, next to
the border in San Diego.
- [Protestor] No human
being will ever be illegal.
- [Will] The protests
come on the heels of that
Congressional delegation visit
to other Texas facilities
where no cameras are allowed,
but Representative Joaquin
Castro snuck in a cellphone
and captured this video.
(speaking in foreign language)
- [Translator] She doesn't
have that (mumbles).
- [Will] Showing women wrapped in
blue sleeping bags on the ground.
The representatives spoke
with some of the women
against Border Patrol orders.
- They were separated from their children,
they've been there over 50 days.
- These women were being
told by CBP officers
to drink out of the toilet.
This is CBP on their best behavior.
- And Will Carr joins us now
live from the US Mexico border,
Will, this new report has
already caught the attention
of Congress.
Democrats are now calling on
immigration officials to testify?
- That's right, Cecilia,
they're moving fast.
They're planning on a hearing next week
where they'll have some tough questions
about the conditions we're
seeing inside of those centers.
They're also planning on looking
at that secret Facebook
group that's been linked
to Border Patrol that had
some disgusting comments
about both migrants and about politicians.
Cecilia?
- Will on this story again
for us tonight, thank you.
Now, to a major development late today
involving the 2020 census.
The Department of Justice
confirming the survey
will be printed without
that controversial question
about US citizenship.
Just yesterday President
Trump said he was looking
into delaying the census
so his administration
could include the citizen question,
no word on the reason
for this sudden reversal.
We'll turn now to that growing backlash
over President Trump's 4th of July plans.
A parade, a concert and
a show of military force
taking place in the nation's capitol.
These tanks are on their way from
Fort Stewart, Georgia by rail.
The president says it's
to honor the military,
but there are questions about
just how much it will cost
and whether his speech
from the Lincoln Memorial
will turn the holiday
into a partisan event.
Here's ABC's chief global
affairs correspondent,
Martha Raddatz.
- [Martha] At the Lincoln Memorial today,
workers hanging bunting
and setting up the presidential podium
for President Trump's unusual 4th of July
address to the nation.
- It's gonna be about this country
and it's a salute to America.
- [Martha] A salute where the
military will play a big part.
(patriotic music)
The president has been fixated
on a grand military display
since he saw the Bastille
Day celebration in France.
Thursday's event on the National Mall
will include military units
and flyovers by Air Force One
and the Blue Angels.
- The best fighter jets in the
world and other planes, too.
And we're gonna have some
tanks stationed outside.
- [Martha] Those tanks
spotted today in Washington
to the dismay of the city council,
which tweeted, "Tanks, but no tanks".
They worry all the military hardware,
even though the 60 ton
tanks will be stationary,
will damage the National Mall.
- He is not respecting the traditions
of this city and region
and it is much resented.
- [Martha] The administration won't say
how much this will cost,
the White House insists the extravaganza
is about patriotism, not politics.
And it is open to the public,
although some VIP tickets
have been given to the
Republican National Committee
to hand out.
So far, nothing for Democrats.
- Okay, Martha Raddatz joins
us now from Washington.
And Martha, the president
tweeting today that
the Pentagon and top
military leaders are thrilled
to be doing this.
Is that what you're
hearing from your sources?
- Well, Cecilia, this is a
time when there are concerns
about the military being politicized,
and some I have talked
to say there is a whiff
of politics in this.
The head of Iraq and
Afghanistan Veterans of America
saying this has the potential
to divide and polarize
and is the very opposite
of what this holiday
should exemplify.
Cecilia?
- Martha Raddatz, thank you.
Overseas now, Russia's
defense ministry is reporting
a deadly fire onboard a
secret Russian submarine.
14 crew members killed including
seven decorated captains.
The fire taking place on one
of the Navy's nuclear powered
deep sea subs in the Pacific.
The submarine has been towed
back to a Russian port.
And back here now, where Nike
is facing a major backlash
after canceling the
release of a new sneaker
that features the so
called "Betsy Ross" flag
over its perceived link
to an era of slavery.
And tonight, Nike could be
facing some unexpected costs.
Here's ABC's Gio Benitez.
- [Gio] Tonight, Nike yanking
this Betsy Ross flag shoe
following public criticism
and a direct appeal
from Colin Kaepernick.
The sneakers were
supposed to launch Monday,
but Kaepernick, one of the
brand's most recognizable
and controversial faces intervened,
reportedly telling execs that the design,
featuring the 13 stars and stripes version
of the American flag was
considered offensive to some,
"because of its connection
to an era of slavery".
Conservatives immediately
taking on Nike and Kaepernick.
Senate majority leader Mitch McConnell
critical of the decision.
- If we're in a political
environment where the
American flag has become
controversial to Americans,
I think we got a problem.
- And Arizona governor Doug Ducey tweeting
that he's pulling roughly $2 million worth
of financial incentives
that were meant for Nike's
new manufacturing plant there.
And Cecilia, in a statement,
Nike tells ABC News
it made the decision to halt distribution
of its 4th of July shoes based on concerns
that it could unintentionally
offend or detract
from the nation's patriotic holiday.
Cecilia?
- Gio Benitez, thank you.
Now, to new developments
in the mystery surrounding
the death of Angels' pitcher Tyler Skaggs.
The 27 year old found dead
in his hotel room in Texas.
Authorities now ruling
out suicide and foul play.
So many paying tribute
today, some leaving flowers
outside the stadium there in Anaheim.
The Angels and the Rangers
taking the field tonight.
ABC's Marcus Moore is there.
- [Marcus] Tonight the Texas Rangers
say they will hold a moment
of silence before tonight's game against
the Los Angeles Angels in
honor of pitcher Tyler Skaggs.
- These guys will be there
fighting for each other
with Tyler weighing heavy
on their hearts tonight.
- [Sports Announcer] Tyler
Skaggs taking the mound
for the Angels.
- The seemingly healthy 27 year old
who wore number 45 seen
here pitching against
the Oakland As over the weekend.
Skaggs, who was supposed
to play in Thursday's
4th of July game was found
dead inside the team hotel.
His death still a mystery,
police telling ABC News
an autopsy has been
completed and so far there is
no evidence to suggest
foul play or suicide.
Just outside the hotel where he died,
flowers and a cap in his memory,
and a growing memorial outside
the Angels' home stadium.
Teammates, family and fans stunned.
- Today's one of the hardest days,
and I know it gets easier
but it's difficult.
- Skaggs leaves behind
his wife Carli Miles
whom he married this past New Year's Eve
just seven months ago.
And Cecilia, authorities say
it could take up to 90 days
to get the results back of that autopsy,
so until then it's a mystery
as to how this young man
died in the prime of his career.
Cecilia?
- Okay, Marcus, thank you.
There is still much more
ahead on World News Tonight
this Tuesday, the shark
scare off the Florida coast.
The family in the water, they
have no idea what's lurking
just a few feet away.
And news tonight about an airline mix up,
the child traveling alone overseas,
the parents claiming the
airline put him on the wrong
connecting flight.
And the total eclipse turning
the skies dark, thousands
of Americans flocking to see it.
- The fact is, every insurance company
hopes you drive safely,
but Allstate actually
helps you drive safely.
With Drivewise.
It lets you know when you go too fast.
(tires screeching)
And brake too hard.
(brakes squealing)
With feedback to help you drive safer,
giving you the power to
actually lower your cost.
Unfortunately, we can't
do anything about that.
Now that you know the truth,
(horn honking)
are you in good hands?
- [Teacher] I'm 52, but
in my mind, I'm still 25.
That's why I take Osteo Bi-Flex,
to keep me moving the way I was made to.
It nourishes and strengthens
my joints for the long term.
- [Narrator] Osteo Bi-Flex,
now in triple strength
plus magnesium.
- Fact, we all love video door bells.
Voice assistants have changed our lives.
We now control our home with a touch.
And you know what's better
than all of these things
by themselves?
- All of these things combined.
- From the most trusted name in security.
- [Both] ADT.
♪ Keep turning it up ♪
♪ I keep turning it up ♪
- Okay, everyone.
Our mission is to provide
complete, balanced nutrition
for strength and energy.
(cheering)
- [Narrator] Great tasting
Ensure with nine grams of protein
and 26 vitamins and minerals.
Ensure, for strength and energy.
- I would get muscle
cramps several times a week
for decades, and in a few days of using
Theraworx Relief the cramps
are gone because it works.
- [Narrator] Get Theraworx Relief today,
in stores everywhere.
- [Announcer] Your brain
changes as you get older,
but Prevagen helps your
brain with an ingredient
originally discovered in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short term memory.
Prevagen, healthier brain, better life.
- I switched to MiraLax
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives forcefully stimulate
the nerves in your colon.
MiraLax works with the water in your body
to unblock your system naturally,
and it doesn't cause bloating, cramping,
gas or sudden urgency.
MiraLax, look for the pink cap.
- Next tonight, a parents' nightmare.
Their son traveling alone to Sweden,
escorted by United Airlines,
but when he changed planes in New Jersey
the boy was instead put
on a flight to Germany.
Here's ABC's David Kerley.
- [David] This is the picture delayed,
when this 14 year old from
Raleigh, North Carolina
was put on the wrong plane in Newark.
Tonight, United Airlines is
apologizing to his family.
A United employee
apparently did not realize
the boy's flight to Sweden had
been moved to another gate.
But still a mystery
tonight, how was Anton Berg
able to get onto a Eurowings
jet headed to Germany?
- They simply failed to
double and cross reference
his documents with who
they perceived he was.
The wrong kid at the wrong
gate with the wrong airline.
- It was the 14 year old who realized
the mistake, because a lot of passengers
were speaking German.
He texted his parents,
his mom started tweeting,
begging United to stop the flight.
It was the 14 year old
who told the flight crew
about the mistake before
takeoff, and the Eurowings jet
returned to the gate.
Anton had to wait for another
flight to get to Sweden
where he was finally
met by his grandmother.
United said in a statement
that it has been in touch
with the family to ensure
the safety of the 14 year old
and apologizes for the event.
Cecilia?
- David Kerley, thank you.
When we come back, the
scare off the coast,
a family in the water,
the danger right there,
just a few feet away.
And NASA takes a big step
towards returning to the moon.
- [DVT Patient] After my
DVT blood clot, I wondered,
is another one around the corner,
or could it be different than I thought?
I wanted to help protect myself.
My doctor recommended Eliquis.
Eliquis is proven to
treat and help prevent
another DVT or PE blood clot.
Almost 98% of patients on
Eliquis didn't experience
another, and Eliquis has
significantly less major bleeding
than the standard treatment.
Eliquis is FDA approved and has both.
- [Announcer] Don't stop Eliquis unless
your doctor tells you to.
Eliquis can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take Eliquis if you
have an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
If you had a spinal
injection while on Eliquis,
call your doctor right
away if you have tingling,
numbness or muscle weakness.
While taking Eliquis, you
may bruise more easily
and it may take longer than
usual for bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden signs of bleeding
like unusual bruising.
Eliquis may increase your
bleeding risk if you take
certain medicines.
Tell your doctor about all planned medical
or dental procedures.
- [DVT Patient] What's around the corner
could be surprising.
Ask your doctor about Eliquis.
- Let's be honest.
You only talk about your insurance
when you complain about it.
- [Patient] Ah ha, ah ha.
- Good point.
That's why Esurance is
making the whole experience
surprisingly painless,
so you never have to talk about it
unless you're the spokesperson.
Esurance, it's surprisingly painless.
(tires screeching)
(engine revving)
(rock music)
- [Announcer] Always there in crunch time.
(horn music)
- I got a certain way I like to do things.
I like Consumer Cellular.
I get unlimited talk and
text for just $25 a month.
With no contract.
They received the J.D.
Power award for highest
customer service again.
- And Consumer Cellular
has been an approved
AARP provider since
2008, so we trust them.
Reliable, nationwide
coverage for way less money?
That's the way--
- We like it.
- [Narrator] Get wireless
the way you like it.
Call, go online, or find us at Target.
- [Dog] My new Beneful Superfood Blend
has me feeling super healthy.
With salmon, cranberries,
oh, but we are not done yet.
Here comes Superfood Wet, with
beef, salmon, and pumpkin.
It's like a superfood sundae.
On a Monday!
- [Narrator] New Beneful Superfood Blend,
dry and wet recipes.
- To The Index, now.
Starting with the shark attack off
New Smyrna Beach, Florida.
Police say an 18 year old
surfer was bitten on the leg.
The injury was not serious.
And in that same area,
just a week earlier,
a shark lurking near this family.
The father flying a drone spotted it.
He immediately yelled for
his wife and three children
to get back to the beach.
You will hear from the
father on tonight's Nightline
and tomorrow on GMA.
Next, the deadly fireworks
accident in Toledo.
Police say a man was killed
by lighting large fireworks
in his front yard with neighborhood
children there watching.
He accidentally set off a mortar
facing in the wrong direction
and was struck in the chest.
And from the earth to the moon.
NASA clearing a major hurdle
with the successful launch
of it's Orion capsule today.
The unmanned capsule blasting
off from Cape Canaveral
on top of a peacekeeper missile,
safely splashing down in the Atlantic.
Orion is designed to take astronauts
back to the moon by 2024.
When we come back, the rare
event in the sky visible
only from two countries
and an uninhabited island.
- [Announcer] ABC World News
Tonight with David Muir,
sponsored in part by Humira.
(alarm buzzing)
- [Announcer] This is your wake up call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis,
month after month the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
Humira can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
Humira targets and blocks
a source of inflammation that
contributes to joint pain
and irreversible damage.
- [Announcer] Humira
can lower your ability
to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes fatal infections
including tuberculosis and
cancers including lymphoma
have happened, as have blood,
liver, and nervous system problems.
Serious allergic reactions and
new or worsening heart failure.
Tell your doctor if you've
been to areas where certain
fungal infections are
common and if you've had TB,
Hepatitis B, are prone to infections
or have flu like symptoms or sores.
Don't start Humira if
you have an infection.
- [Announcer] Help stop
the clock on further
irreversible joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here, right now.
Humira.
- [Announcer] With all day
comfort for all day fun,
Depend Fit Flex underwear
features maximum absorbency,
ultra soft fabric, and
new, beautiful designs
for your best comfort and
protection guaranteed.
Life's better when you're in it.
Be there with Depend.
- [Announcer] This is Fracture.
Just upload an image, place your order,
and it'll show up at your
door, beautifully printed
directly on glass.
And this isn't just another frame,
not just another canvas.
This is new.
This is a fracture.
Visit factureme.com and print one today.
- Each year Americans waste $21 billion
by overpaying on car insurance.
That's why I went to TheZebra.com.
Because while every company claims
to save you money on car insurance,
The Zebra shows you who actually can.
- [Announcer] Compare
car insurance for free
at TheZebra.com today.
(water flowing)
(birds chirping)
(piano music)
- [Announcer] Corey is living
with metastatic breast cancer,
which is breast cancer that
has spread to other parts
of her body.
She's also taking Ibrance
with an aromatase inhibitor,
which is for postmenopausal
women or for men
with HR+ HER2- metastatic breast cancer
as the first hormonal based therapy.
Ibrance plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease
progression versus letrozole.
Patients taking Ibrance can develop
low white blood cell
counts which may cause
serious infections that can lead to death.
Before taking Ibrance, tell
your doctor if you have fever,
chills or other signs of infection,
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects
include low red blood cell
and low platelet counts,
infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth, abnormalities
in liver blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning
or loss, vomiting, rash,
and loss of appetite.
Corey calls it her new normal,
because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about Ibrance,
the number one prescribed
FDA approved oral combination
treatment for HR+ HER2- MBC.
- [Robin] Imagine a good
morning spent with friends.
What's better than that?
Imagine knowing what's
coming next in the day ahead.
Well, I get to live this each morning.
Together with you, imagine that.
And that's what makes it
such a Good Morning America.
- Finally, tonight a
stunning show in the sky
that only a small part
of the world could see,
including our Rob Marciano.
- This is the moment day became night
in South America.
There it is, we have totality.
The moon passing perfectly between
the Earth and the sun,
a bullseye blocking out
all but the glowing edge
of the sun's corona,
the hills and valley around us going dark.
It's gotten so dark you can see stars,
and it's cold.
Temperatures have dropped
a good 10 degrees in
the last 20 minutes.
The moon's shadow sweeping
along a nearly 7000 mile path
across the Pacific,
hitting the coast of Chile
at 4:38 PM.
Nightfall for two and a half minutes.
You hear the birds?
The birds are confused.
It's the first one since the
coast to coast US eclipse
of 2017,
and many Americans traveled
here to see another.
- Totality's very spiritual
for a lot of people,
and once you see one, you
wanna see the next one.
- [Rob] Why the allure?
- It's a multisensory experience unlike
anything else nature has to offer.
- The next total solar eclipse in the US?
April 2024.
Cecilia?
- Well, we'll be waiting,
okay, thank you Rob.
Thank you for watching, I'm Cecilia Vega
here in New York.
I hope to see you right
back here tomorrow,
have a great evening.
- A fortune can be won on
the turn of a single card.
- [Announcer] Pick high or low.
- Higher!
- [Announcer] Rake in the dough.
- This is a fight to the death.
It's not.
- [Announcer] Joel
McHale hosts Card Sharks,
Wednesdays on ABC.
- [Announcer] Get the deals now during the
Great American Tent Sale at Sears.
Save up to 40% off appliances
like this Kenmore fridge for $1299.99.
Plus, get $300 cash back
in points over 20 weeks.
Shop in store or at sears.com
to start making your
summer moments matter.
- Popeyes' new Parmesan ranch
Double Dippers, nice move.
- He's double dipping.
- In ranch and Parmesan.
- Do you guys wanna try some of this?
- [Announcer] Now you can
double dip six boneless wings
with my $5 Parmesan ranch Double Dippers.
♪ Love that chicken from Popeyes ♪
- [Announcer] How do you
celebrate the 4th of July?
Show us with a picture.
Just upload your best shots
using our ABC 7 news app.
(chiming)
- [Announcer] Get ready for clearance.
It's the Honda 4th of July sales event.
Accords on clearance, Civics on clearance,
CR-Vs and HR-Vs on clearance.
Even the third row Pilot is on clearance,
with features on clearance,
safety on clearance
and selection on clearance.
Like an.