- Well thanks so much to
you for joining us today,
I'm Jim Sciutto.
You can follow me on Twitter @JimSciutto.
At This Hour With Kate Bolduan
starts right now.
(dramatic music)
- Hello everyone, I'm Kate Boldaun.
Thanks so much for joining me.
A ticking time bomb, that is
what federal investigators warn
in a new report about the
dangerous overcrowding
occurring in government border facilities.
A government report,
not an advocacy group,
not Democratic members of Congress,
not attorneys representing migrants,
this is a 16 page report
compiled by the Inspector General
of the Department of Homeland Security.
Look at these images
that we're showing right here.
What they found is shocking.
Mass overcrowding of children and adults,
some with no access to
showers or clean clothes.
No laundry facilities.
It's all detailed in the report.
Some children with no access
to warm meals for days.
Adults forced into standing
room only conditions
for a week, the report says.
Officials describe the migrants
even as banging on cell windows
and holding up signs for help.
And then there are these images.
These are images drawn by children
who recently were released
from border facilities.
The drawings appear to show children,
you know exactly what your eyes tell you.
In cages, in jail.
The American Academy of Pediatrics
released these pictures,
saying that these facilities,
in their words, are no place for children.
It's a painful reminder
of what these children
are going through and are
going through right now.
Let's get straight over
to CNN's Nick Valencia.
He's at a border facility
in El Paso, Texas.
Nick, what's the very latest?
- Well, it's a bit of
breaking news this morning.
We're hearing from acting DHS
secretary, Kevin McAleenan
about those social media posts.
Remember earlier this week Kate
we reported, ProPublica,
the investigative team
first reported about this
closed Facebook group
that featured current
and former they say, Border Patrol agents
making lewd comments, derogatory comments,
racially inflammatory comments,
joking about dead migrants.
Well, now Kevin McAleenan
the acting DHS secretary
tweeting this this morning.
"I have directed an
immediate investigation,
"and as the U.S. Border
Patrol Cheif has made clear,
"any employee found to have
compromised the public's trust
"in our law enforcement mission
will be held accountable."
What is a little bit unclear
to us at this moment is
we were under the understanding
that earlier this week
an investigation had
already been under way.
The posts were said to have
been turned over to the
Internal Affairs at CBP, DHS.
Inspector General has also said to have
gotten their hands on
these social media posts.
A broader question though Kate,
we're also wondering if he's calling
for an investigation into
these social media posts?
When will he call for an
investigation into the conditions
in these Border Patrol facilities?
And speaking on that, it was yesterday
that I spoke to a long time veteran
El Paso Border Patrol agent who said
that they are just tired
of seeing the conditions
that migrants are being held
in and decided to speak out.
So long as we concealed their identity.
You're taking a big risk by doing this.
- [Agent] Yes, but America needs to know.
They need to know the truth.
- [Nick] A Border Patrol
agent who's had enough.
In a CNN exclusive interview,
the veteran agent who
agreed to go on camera
only if their identity was
concealed, expressed disgust
at a closed Facebook group
reportedly comprised of thousands
of current and former agents.
ProPublica the first to expose the group,
I'm 10-15, where members
shared lewd and sexist content
about Latina members of congress including
Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez.
The agent telling CNN being derogatory is
part of the Border Patrol culture,
even hearing a supervisor
joke about dead migrants.
- [Agent] He was making fun of them.
- Saying what?
- [Agent] That, what
difference does it make,
it's just another life.
He made a comment also
regarding running over illegals
and I'm like, you cannot run over people.
- [Nick] In describing the conditions
inside the El Paso detention facilities,
the agent compared them to a zoo.
- [Agent] The holding facility, the cells,
they are, what I would say, filthy.
We have a maintenance and cleaning crew
that clean the general
area, like the hallways,
but I have never seen
them cleaning pampers,
or cleaning toilets in the cells
or cleaning sinks in the cell.
Sometimes you go in a cell
and there is trash everywhere.
- There are those in leadership
in Customs and Border Protection,
- [Agent] Yes.
- [Nick] They say, that
migrants are getting
basic human rights.
What do you say to leaders who are saying,
migrants are getting basic human rights?
- [Agent] What is basic human rights?
Toilet paper?
Water from the sink?
Wearing the same clothing for days?
I remember when there used
to be a processing center,
where we used to have,
especially in winter,
we used to have these blankets,
and 10 different aliens
would use the same blanket.
We would recycle them.
We'd put them in a bag and
they wouldn't get wash.
- I feel like, you know, multiple
times during our interview
you've sort of stared off in the distance
and you've thought about
some things that you've seen.
It seems as though there are things
that you might take home with you.
- [Agent] Everyday.
- Like what?
- [Agent] The kids.
- [Nick] What about the kids?
- [Agent] You know, they just want hope.
They want to believe in something.
They want to feel sure.
- Do you support President
Trump's immigration policies?
- [Agent] President Trump
is our Commander-in-chief,
and unless he's unethical, illegal,
or immoral we should obey.
- [Nick] The question is, at what cost?
Customs and Border Protection
did not directly respond
to those allegations, Kate,
but they did say that
they're handing them over
to the Office of the Inspector General.
- Nick, thanks so much.
Really great reporting down
there, really appreciate it.
Joining me right now,
to discuss this further,
is Congressman Marc Veasey of Texas.
He was among the Democratic
lawmakers who visited
some of the border detention facilities
in his state this week.
Congressman, I was just
seeing you shaking your head.
- Yeah, I mean, just hearing that, I mean,
how can you hear that and it
not just break your heart?
I mean, it's awful.
And based on what I saw, on
my trip, day before yesterday,
I 100% believe him.
They did everything they could
to give us the there's
nothing here to see tour,
but when you talked to
migrants that were in custody,
they told us first hand
that they were being told
to drink out of toilets
when they were thirsty,
that there were kids that were
walking around in clothing
where there was mucus just from
days and days worth of mucus
and other debris on their clothing.
Showers being denied for days.
They told us that they
could shower anytime,
at least once a day,
but what we were told was
that they were being denied
showers for days by migrants,
and you know, based on this Facebook post,
how can you not believe that
the migrants were telling us
the truth, and now based on
what this Border Patrol agent
was just telling us and the IG report,
I mean, something has to change.
- Well, let's talk about
that, but before we get there,
on top of those two things,
there's something else that
has come out, these images,
these drawings from the
American Academy of Pediatrics.
They released these pictures of drawings
that young children made
once they were released,
but made of their time in custody.
I mean, you can see with your own eyes,
what it clearly looked like
to them and more importantly,
what it felt like to them to be in there.
What do you say to that when you see this?
- Yeah, well, I can't see the images,
but I can tell you that we saw
young children that appeared
to me to be three or four years old
that were in holding cells.
Holding cells similar
to what you would see
at a county lock-up.
And again, just based on the IG's report
and the interviews that we just heard,
there's no question in my
mind that these children
are being treated very poorly
and I think that it also
illustrates that President Trump
will do anything that he can
to try to appease his base
when it comes to immigration
and that he is using this migrants,
as pawns in a political game
and that is just absolutely
sick and it has to stop now.
And I will tell you that one of the things
that has to change today
is that members of Congress
need to be able to go and
visit these facilities
without 48 hour notice.
Right now, we have to give 48 hour notice.
We need to be able to
go into these facilities
whenever we want to
and we can fly down there on our own dime,
we can fly down there at
the spur of the moment--
- I actually have been wondering
about this, Congressman.
- When we hear about this allegations.
- It's really interesting
actually that you bring this up
because I've been wondering this.
Coming from the IG report,
where they did surprise visits
at five facilities and
that's what they found.
And even with the amount of
notice that you were given,
that you had to give to
go into this facility,
and the stories that you were told,
I'm starting to wonder if you just,
because journalists can't
go in there with cameras,
that's the thing I continue
to have to say to our viewers.
Why don't you just make a tour of it,
why don't you just give
that 48 hours notice
and make a tour of it
and keep visiting these
facilities over and over again
because maybe that is
what would bring about,
maybe that is what would
bring about change?
- Yeah, I think that again,
obviously more tours would be helpful,
but not having to give the notice.
I mean, if I wanted to
go down there right now
and visit that facility at Clint,
or any of them along the border,
I need to be able to,
as a member of Congress,
we have oversight of these committees,
and the game that they're playing.
And I personally feel like the reason
why they're playing games
is that they feel empowered
by this president and Stephen Miller,
who's his so-called immigration tzar.
- But you do have someone
appointed by the President
as well, the new Acting Chief
of the Department of Homeland Security,
who he says he's acting,
in talking about the Facebook postings,
that secret Facebook page.
He's directed an investigation
and he says that anyone
who's done wrong should be
and will be held accountable.
We learned that today.
Do you applaud him?
- Yeah, no absolutely.
He is certainly saying the right thing
when it comes to that.
We need to see it followed up with action.
Of course, you probably
saw that Elijah Cummings,
who's the Chair of the
Oversight Committee,
that he's going to conduct investigations,
that the acting secretary
said that he is going
to conduct investigations.
And not only do people
need to be disciplined,
people need to be fired.
I mean, I can't tell
you, Kate, just the fact,
knowing that some of the
people that were supposed to be
our security for that day,
when we were at the press
conference, and all of the people
that were wearing the MAGA hats
were screaming obscenities at us,
that those were supposed to
be our security personnel
and those are the people that
are supposed to be in charge
of making sure these migrants
are being treated humanely,
and they're a part of that Facebook page.
That's just absolutely unacceptable.
So, when investigations are conducted,
and I hope that they will
be conducted very swiftly,
people need to be terminated and, again,
depending on what is found out,
there may need to be some people
that need to be prosecuted.
- Well, one thing that we do know,
is there's something like
9500 members of that Facebook page,
but we don't know exactly
who those Facebook pages,
who those postings are from,
who those people are in real life,
that is part of the investigation
and that is what Kevin McAleenan says
they're gonna get to the bottom of.
There's so much more to this,
especially from this IG report.
I just cannot turn away from
it and no one else should.
Congressman, thank you comin' on.
Let us know when you go on your next tour.
- Absolutely.
- We have another story, though,
that we're following this morning.
CNN has learned that
military chiefs have concerns
over what President Trump's
Fourth of July event
is turning into.
A source with direct knowledge says
that while planning the event,
Pentagon leaders expressed reservations
about putting military hardware,
like tanks and other armored
vehicles, on display.
Those concerns, I mean,
they don't appear to have
had much of an impact
as we know, tanks are
already on the National Mall
as of this morning.
So, what's this all going to cost?
That is also unclear.
CNN's Tom Foreman, he's in Washington,
at the National Mall for us.
- Hey Kate, preparations
are underway all up and down
the National Mall here
where things like this big
pieces of military hardware
are being brought in as
the President has requested
to have a great show of
American power and influence.
But his critics are saying
what this really is all about
is a great show of his ego.
The iconic fireworks
over the National Mall
will be moved to a new spot.
All flights will be grounded
at Washington's Reagan National Airport
for more than two hours
and three times the usual
number of National Guard troops
will be deployed for security.
All so President Donald
Trump can be the centerpiece
for DC's Fourth of July celebration,
giving an unprecedented speech
at the Lincoln Memorial.
- We're gonna have a great
Fourth of July in Washington DC.
It'll be like no other.
- [Tom] For all the costly changes,
it's still not precisely
what he wanted early on,
a grand military parade, as
seen in other some countries,
such as France, Russia, and North Korea,
but cost estimates for
that plan quickly ran into
tens of millions of dollars.
The DC City Council, mindful
of expensive street damage
howled, "No tanks".
The Park Service has remained quiet
about how much it will cost to take on
the additional requirements.
And the Pentagon is not
discussing the price tag
for a flyover by the Blue Angels,
a plane that serves as Air Force One,
some other aircraft,
and a couple of tanks and troop carriers
that will also be there, but
simply parked near the Mall.
- We wanna bring millions
of people into the city
and we want people to
come who love our country!
Those are the people we want.
- [Tom] The President tweeting,
"The Pentagon and our great
Military Leaders are thrilled,"
after asking the chiefs of every branch
to stand with him during the celebration.
The Pentagon, not saying
which, if any, are going.
And adding to the frustration of those
who claim the traditionally
non-partisan event
is being hijacked by Team
Trump, the White House,
and the Republican National Committee,
are reportedly giving VIP access
to favored friends and colleagues.
Democrats say on this scorching week,
they are largely being frozen out.
The White House response.
- This is a public event,
it's open to the public.
- One part of the public I don't
think they're going to like
too much, Kate, is protestors
have received a permit
to fly that baby Trump
balloon over everything.
So that will also be up in the air here,
no doubt to the displeasure
of the White House.
Kate.
- Tom, thank you so much.
So, it is of course the Fourth
of July as we're discussing,
and we are of course in the
middle of an election season
so you know what that means.
All roads lead to Iowa!
At least for almost everyone.
Most of the top Democratic
presidential contenders
converging on the state right now,
what does that look like on the ground?
And what are Iowa caucus goers,
what are they talkin' about right now?
(intense music)
- My experience with
USAA has been excellent.
They really appreciate military families
and it really shows.
- With all that USAA offers,
why go with anybody else?
We know their rates are good.
We know that they're always
gonna take care of us.
- It was instant savings
and I should have changed a long time ago.
- It was funny because when we would call,
another insurance company they would say,
Oh we can't beat USAA.
- We're the Weber family.
- We're the Tenney's.
- We're the Hail's and
we're USAA members for life.
- [Announcer] Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
- [Announcer] Prestige creams
not living up to the hype?
Olay Regenerist shatters the competition.
Big hype, big price, big deal.
Olay Regenerist, hydrates
skin better than creams
costing over 100, 200, and even $400.
(upbeat music)
For skin that looks
younger than it should.
Fact check this ad in Good Housekeeping.
Olay Regenerist.
Now, try Olay Hydrating Eye.
Hydrates better than the
number one prestige eye cream.
- [Man] With my Hepatitis C,
I felt I couldn't be at
my best for my family.
In only eight weeks with
Mavyret, I was cured,
and left those doubts behind.
- [Woman] I faced reminders
of my Hep C everyday,
but in only eight weeks
with Mavyret, I was cured.
- [Man] Even hanging with friends
I was worried about my Hep C,
but in only eight weeks
with Mavyret, I was cured.
- [Announcer] Mavyret is
the only eight-week cure
for all common types of Hep C.
Before starting Mavyret,
your doctor will test if
you'd had Hepatitis B,
which may flare up and
cause serious liver problems
during and after treatment.
Tell your doctor if
you've had Hepatitis B,
a liver or kidney transplant,
other liver problems,
HIV 1, or other medical conditions,
and all medicines you take,
including herbal supplements.
Don't take Mavyret with
Atazanavir or rifampin
or if you've had certain liver problems.
Common side effects include
headache and tiredness.
- With Hep C behind me, I feel free.
- Fearless.
- And there's no looking
back because I am cured.
- [Announcer] Talk to
your doctor about Mavyret.
- [Announcer] Most people think
a button is just a button.
(dramatic music)
That a speaker is just a speaker.
Or that the journey
can't be the destination.
Most people haven't driven a Lincoln.
- [Announcer] Discover the
Lincoln approach to craftsmanship
at the Lincoln Summer Invitation.
Right now get 0% APR on
all 2019 Lincoln vehicles,
plus no payments for up to 90 days.
Only at your Lincoln dealer.
- We found the perfect new home
and we wanted to move fast,
but we didn't feel
confident making an offer
until we knew our other home would sell.
- [Announcer] Introducing,
Simple Sale by HomeLight.
With Simple Sale, cash buyers
compete to make you an offer
whenever you're ready to sell.
There's no prep, no
hassle, no uncertainty.
- We sold our home in under
a week and it was so easy.
And that perfect new
home we found, we got it.
- [Announcer] To see
your Simple Sale price,
visit homelight.com/simple today.
- [Announcer] Instead of
going to school every morning,
what if school could come to you?
Because learning happens
anywhere and everywhere.
K12 powered schools provide
a tuition-free, full-time,
online public school education.
- It's public school at home.
- [Announcer] Visit k12.com to learn more.
- My students are ready
to accept the challenge
and they get all the
attention that they deserve.
- [Announcer] Students benefit
from personalized support
from state certified teachers.
- That, to me, is a huge support for me.
Honestly, she's just happier.
- I can have more time with my family
and do gymnastics.
- [Announcer] K12's curriculum is designed
to engage students, to challenge them,
and it's tuition free.
- [Mom] It's been a huge
change in her life and ours.
- [Announcer] So visit k12.com today
and join the over one million K12 students
who have chosen public school at home.
Tuition-free and available in most states.
- I have always wanted to do this.
- This is gonna be awesome!
- [Both] Let's do this!
- Babe, what are you doing?
- Gonna demo the bathroom.
Who are you?
- The Bath Fitter installer, remember?
Bath Fitter custom made our
new bath to fit perfectly
over the new old one so
there's no demo or mess.
- Impressive.
- Wait, so no demo?
- Sorry, man.
- [Announcer] Bath Fitter
will remodel your bath
with no messy demolition
in as little as one day.
Call now or visit bathfitter.com
for a free in-home consultation.
- [Announcer] Closed
captioning brought to you
by Theraworx Relief.
Prevent and relieve muscle cramps.
- I would get muscle cramps
several times a week for decades.
Using Theraworx Relief,
the cramps are gone.
- [Announcer] Get Theraworx Relief today
in stores everywhere.
- If you're running for president,
there are some general rules of the road,
and this is in no way a complete list.
You need get used to
shakin' hands, lots of 'em,
you need to get used to
kissing really cute babies,
and you better get
yourself to Iowa if it is
the Fourth of July.
Seven candidates are campaigning
across the state today,
including four of the five
top tier in the latest polling
out of Iowa.
All crisscrossing the
state to make their pitch,
capitalize on their debate bounce,
or make up ground for their
recent drop-off if you will.
So, let's go there.
Joining me right now is
Chief Politics Reporter
for the Des Moines Register,
Brianne Pfannenstiel
Brianne, thanks for being here.
- Thanks for having me.
- So the latest polling
numbers we have out of Iowa
really show that the race has reset.
We've got Kamala Harris
seeing a big bounce,
launching into second place,
Biden in the front still
but seeing a real slide in support.
What are you hearing on the ground.
Is Kamala's rise for real?
- Well I think you're
hearing a lot of voters
who are really interested in Kamala.
You know, even in Iowa a lot of people
are really tuning into this whole process
for the first time during
the national debates.
They're seeing this candidates
lined up side by side,
and so they're getting their first sense
of how they interact, how
they appeal to voters,
and so people are really
interested in Kamala right now,
they're interested to see what
she's gonna be talking about
during her campaign swing here.
She's got several events across the state
so we'll be following her
but Joe Biden is also in town
and so people also are curious to see
how he's going to respond
to this new pressure.
- That's a great question.
The candidate who seems to be
also facing some real trouble
in Iowa right now is Bernie Sanders.
In a pre-debate, Sanders was holding out,
holding on in second place at 16% support.
Post-debate the USA
Today Suffolk University
poll out of Iowa, he
dropped to fourth place,
and for the first time hitting
into the single digits there.
You were just at a Sanders event.
What about his message isn't
connecting with folks there?
What are you hearing?
- Well, I think there's a
little bit of a disconnect
because the people who like Bernie Sanders
really like Bernie Sanders.
You go to some events and
the people who are there
are very much for him.
They're committed to him in a
way that they're not committed
to a lot of these other
candidates on the ground here.
You go to these events and people say,
you know I'm shopping around,
I wanna hear from more people,
I'm trying to see what they have to say
but you go to a Bernie Sanders event
and they say, I'm here for Bernie
I'm planning to caucus for him.
So while he certainly slipped in the polls
I wouldn't necessarily underestimate
how much support he has here
in Iowa from his core base.
These polls are showing him slipping
and so he may need to adjust
his message a little bit
but I also think we're gonna be seeing
a lot of movement between now
and caucus day in those polls.
- And also one thing we
know about Bernie Sanders
is adjusting his message is
not something that he does.
He's had the same message for a long time
and that's what his
supporters love about him.
So watching the debate of course
there were a million issues
in the two hour or four
hours over the two nights
that the candidates
cared about, talked about
and were asked about.
Is there one or two issues
that you are hearing
most about from Democrats in Iowa
as they're facing this big
field of Democrats right now
to choose from?
- Yeah, and we try to track this a lot.
You know, what questions are
Iowans asking at these events?
What's top of mind for them
and we try to do a lot
of polling of the crowds
just one on one as reporters
and so what we hear every single time
is healthcare is a huge issue
and so where they fall on healthcare,
where they want these candidates
to stand on say Medicare for all is vast.
There's a lot of differences
in what they want
but healthcare is, I
would say, the top issue
that we're hearing about
and I think that's followed really closely
by climate change right now.
- Oh, that's really interesting to see,
to hear that from Democrats
and can be really telling on maybe
what the messaging will be that we hear
from all the Democrats
that are there right now.
Trump won Iowa in the general in 2016,
before that Obama won twice in Iowa.
The president was back recently
holding rallies in Iowa.
How is his level of
support in Iowa right now?
What are you hearing
about President Trump?
- Well, among Republicans his support
has stayed very strong in Iowa.
You know, all of our polling
from the time he was elected
to where he's at right now
he gets in the 80s, 80%
support among Republicans
who really approve of the job he's doing.
So to the degree that Iowa
Republicans supported him
in 2016 we haven't seen that wavering.
I think there are some
republicans who are skeptical,
certainly some independents
who are shopping around
but among his core base
we've really seen those numbers steady.
- Brianne, much more to come.
Thank you so much.
Good luck tracking all these candidates
for the next couple days, thank you.
Programming note for all of you.
A CNN exclusive.
Former Vice President
Joe Biden and his wife
Dr. Jill Biden will be
sitting down with Chris Cuomo.
That interview airs Friday morning at six
and 8:00 a.m. Eastern only on CNN.
Still to come for us the Supreme Court
blocked a question about
citizenship from the U.S. Census.
We've talked a lot about that
since that decision happened.
The administration then conceded defeat
and said that it was
going ahead and printing
the Census forms without
having the question
or without fighting it anymore,
but President Trump just now
says that the fight isn't over.
What is going on here?
We'll be back.
- [Announcer] This is Rick Blonquest.
His life is pretty comfortable.
Then he laid on a Serta
and realized his life
was only just sort of comfortable.
- I've been living a lie.
- [Announcer] The Serta
iComfort Hybrid Mattress.
Not just sort of comfortable,
Serta comfortable.
- Okay, I'll admit I didn't keep my place
as clean as I would like
'cause I'm way too busy.
Who's got the time to chase
around dirt, dust and hair?
So now I use Heavy Duty
Swiffer Sweeper and Dusters.
For hard to reach places
Duster makes it easy to clean.
It captures dust in one swipe.
Ha, gotcha!
And Sweeper Heavy Duty cloths lock away
twice as much dirt and dust.
It gets stuff deep in the
grooves other tools can miss.
You know what?
My place is a lot cleaner now.
Stop cleaning, start Swiffering.
- He was diagnosed with a large tumor.
St. Jude gave us our son back.
This place is saving children every day.
(speaks in foreign language)
- This is a perfectly healthy baby
and then he gets cancer
three months later.
- [Announcer] One in
five children diagnosed
with cancer in the U.S. will not survive.
You can join the battel to save lives
by supporting St. Jude
Children's Research Hospital.
- Without St. Jude and
without the research
they've done I may not have my daughter.
- [Announcer] Families never
receive a bill from St. Jude
for treatment, travel, housing or food
because all a family should worry about
is helping their child live.
Please call or go online right now
and become a St. Jude partner in hope
for only $19 a month.
- I hope they find the cure for cancer
so you can go back to being
normal and be stronger.
- They share their research so it's saving
children around the world.
- [Announcer] When you join
with your credit or debit card
right now we'll send you
this St. Jude T-Shirt
you can wear to show your support
for the children of St. Jude.
- To people who've donated
I would say, thank you
from the bottom of my heart.
I wish I could shake each
and every one of your hands.
- My biggest hope, if
I can really be honest,
is for a cure.
I am longing for the day.
- St. Jude won't stop until
no child dies from cancer.
- My son is with me today
because people are giving.
You're giving a parent their child back.
- [Announcer] Go online or call
with your $19 monthly gift.
Become a St. Jude partner in hope.
- [Announcer] Oh my, this
Heinz Mayonnaise is so creamy
one day you'll tell
your grandkids about it,
and they'll say, "Grandpa just
tell us about Humpty Dumpty."
And you'll say, "He broke
his pelvis or whatever.
"Now back to my creamy Heinz Mayonnaise."
Heinz Mayonnaise, unforgettably creamy.
- Everyone loves a throwback
but I haven't worn that suit
in awhile, or those shoes.
Luckily I still have them
because the clothes that
once gave you confidence
can help someone get their
career back on track.
So throwback and donate
at Men's Wearhouse today.
- [Boy] How's it going?
- How's what going?
The John Hughes scripts, they
just jumped off the page.
I remember reading, "Sixteen Candles"
in the back of my parents car
just stretched out on
the seat cracking up.
♪ Limu Emu ♪
- [Announcer] And Doug.
- What do all these people
have in common, Limu?
(paper rustling)
Exactly, nothing.
They're completely different people.
That's why they make
customized car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay for what they need.
(change clatters)
Yes, and they could save a ton.
You've done it again Limu.
- [Announcer] Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty, Liberty, Liberty ♪
- Tell him we're flexible.
- Don't worry, my Dutch is okay.
- Just okay?
- Mm-hmm.
(speaks in foreign language)
- Tell him we need this merger.
- It's happening.
- [Announcer] Just okay is not okay
especially when it comes to your network.
AT&T is America's best wireless network
according to America's biggest test.
Now with 5G evolution,
the first step to 5G.
More for your thing.
That's our thing.
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- President Trump is
refusing to accept defeat.
Denying that his
administration is backing down
just a day after it
announced a huge about face
that it is going to be moving forward
with printing the Census without including
the citizenship question
that Trump officials had
fought so hard to include.
Moments ago President Trump spoke out
denying the position of
his own administration.
Tweeting this in part.
"We are absolutely
moving forward as we must
"because of the importance of
this answer to this question."
Aside from the fac that that
seems a little bit confusing
this is like the second tweet
that he had about this today
and he is saying that
they're gonna fight on.
So, he's not giving up now?
But what can he do?
The forms are being printed according
to the Commerce Department,
and the Supreme Court
told the administration that they had
to go back to the drawing board
if they even wanted to
consider this question again.
Joining me right now to
hopefully get some answers here
CNN Supreme Court
reporter, Ariane de Vogue.
Ariane, what can the
president do at this point?
- Well, those tweets
certainly seem to leave open
the possibility but he might be having
to pull a rabbit out of a hat here, Kate
because yesterday Secretary
Ross's statement was definitive
and the Department of
Justice told the court
that the decision was final
according to plaintiff's lawyers
and one of the reasons is, is
they have big hurdles here.
They have a Census official who testified
that waiting until October
to print those questionnaires
could jeopardize the
administration of the Census
and he also said that it
would take a lot of resources
to do so, and on top of that there's two
collateral legal proceedings
happening in the lower courts.
In New York one judge
is considering sanctions
against the government for new evidence
that had been recently disclosed
that suggested that the decision
might have been politically motivated.
And another judge in Maryland
he was considering at
least reopening the case,
more deposition, more testimony.
A government official told me today
that the decision was
final, that they just looked
at these deadlines and the
possibility of more injunctions
and they thought it wasn't realistic.
But maybe what the
president is talking about
is what the Census officials
have argued all along.
Keep in mind Census officials had said,
there's other ways to
get this information.
It doesn't have to be on the question.
For instance they can
get it through other data
with the government, and there's a survey
that goes out to some households
and asks the questions.
So maybe that's what the
president is talking about
but it's a little unclear right now, Kate.
- A little unclear?
It's a lot unclear if you will, Ariane
and I think this goes into the category
of I don't know if it's dream world
versus reality but in the very least
because the Commerce Secretary
says the Census papers
are being printed without the question
it's at least maybe don't listen
to what the president says
just look at what he actually does
and let's see if he actually
tries to fight this change
just to do anything about it
or he just wants to tweet about it.
Thanks, Ariane.
- Thanks, Kate.
- Coming up for us Democratic
presidential candidate,
Mayor Pete Buttigieg
facing new criticism now
over a police shooting in his
hometown, South Bend, Indiana.
That new criticism now coming
from his own police department.
Coming up one of the police officers
who's calling for the
mayor to recuse himself
from the investigation.
We'll be right back.
- [Woman] Thanks Golden Corral.
Dan gets a slow smoked sirloin
and my little trio are as
happy as shrimp, oops clams
and mom got it all.
Hook, line and sirloin.
The slow smoked sirloin and shrimp trio.
Golden Corral, the only one for everyone.
- [Announcer] Celebrate
your independent style
at Lumber Liquidator's Flooring Company.
Save 36% on premium Bellawood
Carriage House White Ash.
And save on Stone Look Waterproof floors.
Plus get 12 months special financing.
Lumber Liquidators,
beautiful floors for less.
- Many sunglasses may actually
make it harder to see.
And if they don't cut the
road glare it can be deadly.
This is Battle Vision by Atomic Beam.
Inspired by U.S. soldiers
that depend on clear vision
to hit their targets.
Hi, I'm Hunter Ellis
and I wear Battle Vision
by Atomic Beam for crystal clear vision
when it matters most.
Battle Vision lets you
see in high definition
and even blocks dangerous
glare helping to keep you safe.
Unlike regular glasses these high tech
HD polarized lenses help you see objects
the naked eye can't detect.
Out on the water and the
reflection's too much?
Battle Vision's polarized lenses
filter out reflected light
knocking down glare so you can see clearly
in ultra high definition.
They help eliminate glare, enhance color
and provide UV protection for
exceptional optical clarity.
Battle Vision can be twisted
and tortured without breaking.
The lenses can withstand
hard drops and knocks.
Sand, rocks, glass, even metal
are no match for Battle Vision.
Look, regular glasses just
make everything darker
so whether you're out skiing
or out on the open road
cut the glare and see with Battle Vision.
From riding your motorcycle
to riding your bike,
playing tennis or target practice
battle through the glare
and see with sharp clarity.
Similar sunglasses can cost hundreds.
Call or click now and get
Battle Vision by Atomic Beam
the ultimate tactical
eyewear for just 19.99.
Order right now
and we'll double this entire
offer absolutely free.
One to wear and a spare
with no additional fees.
100% free.
You'll also get a lifetime guarantee.
Battle Vision by Atomic
Beam with lifetime guarantee
is just 19.99, order now.
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-503-7261,
that's 1-800-503-7261.
Call or visit BuyBattlevision.com.
So call 1-800-503-7261,
that's 1-800-503-7261.
Order now.
♪ Ba, Ba, Ba, Ba, Bulbhead ♪
- Hey, I'm Zach, CEO of Roman.
Some health issues are
tough to talk about.
With Roman you can go online
chat with a physician and if
treatment is right for you
we'll ship FDA approved
medication right to your door.
Roman, let's take care of it.
♪ Limu Emu ♪
- [Announcer] And Doug.
- Exactly, Liberty Mutual
customizes your car insurance
so you only pay for what you need.
- Nice, but what's up with your partner?
- Oh, we just spend all
day telling everyone
how we customize car insurance
because no two people are alike.
So Limu gets a little confused
when he sees another bird
that looks exactly like him, yeah.
He'll figure it out.
- [Announcer] Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty, Liberty, Liberty ♪
- I was missing teeth,
it was painful to chew.
I cut up my food very
small and I would feel
more and more limited.
- I know she felt that she
was holding people back.
We couldn't go where we
wanted to go out to eat.
- [Sue] I knew I had to try something
and that's what originally
drove me to Clear Choice.
- When a patient comes in
for their free consultation
oftentimes they're not
happy with their dentures.
Dental implant procedures,
they're more permanent.
The materials are stronger,
they're made with a higher
level of technology.
- [Sue] Implants are like normal teeth.
I mean there was no pain.
Dentures could never fit right.
With the implants you don't take them out
so there's no worry about them slipping
when you actually can eat
and smile as much as
you want it's wonderful.
(gentle music)
- [Announcer] Closed captioning brought
to you by MesoBook.com.
- Mesothelioma is all we do.
For over 10 years we have offered
a free book on Mesothelioma.
Call 1-800-259-9374.
(dramatic music)
- South Bend, Indiana Mayor Pete Buttigieg
is rolling out a plan today to
promote the call to service.
A plan that would greatly expand
voluntary public service
programs in the country
with a goal, according to the campaign,
of attracting a quarter
of a million Americans
to serve in the near term
and potentially more down the road.
We're talking about programs
like AmeriCorps and the Peace Corps.
But while he's promoting
the call to service
the mayor is also dealing
with continued questions
about his leadership back home.
Racial tension flaring up
in South Bend last month
after a white police officer
shot and killed a black man
who approached the officer
with a knife raised,
that's according to the police.
The case has fueled
anger from the community
and activists and police.
Just yesterday the Fraternal
Order of Police in South Bend
called for Buttigieg to remove himself
from any involvement
in that investigation.
Buttigieg addressed the
controversy again yesterday.
- Events compel me to acknowledge
that whatever we've done
has not been nearly enough.
As long as a traffic stop
is a completely different experience
for a black driver than
it is for a white driver
we know we have not done nearly enough.
We know that as long
as police departments,
and this is true of my own,
do not reflect the community
they serve in their makeup
then we have not done enough.
I accept responsibility
for the work that is left to be done.
- Joining me right now is the president
of the South Bend
Fraternal Order of Police.
Police Sergeant Harvey Mills.
Sergeant, thank you for being here.
- Thank you, Kate.
- In your statement yesterday
in calling for the mayor
to pull himself off
of the investigation you
said that the mayor is quote,
"More concerned about boosting his own
"presidential political campaign
"than insuring a fair investigation."
why do you think that?
- Ma'am, several of
the comments he's made,
he's already called for the,
or he's already stated that this officer
will be held accountable,
well the investigation's
not even complete.
This officer was justified
in defending himself
against a man with an
eight inch hunting knife.
It's just absurd that he would
make statements like that
as well as calling all officers racist.
- I wanted to get to that
because I heard you say that.
I've heard you say that
you think that the mayor
has called all officers racist
and I looked back at what
he said during the debate
and I also looked at
what he said on Monday
and he was talking about systemic racism
and here's how he explained it on Monday.
He said that, "Every
mayor works in the shadows
"of systemic racism.
"Every resident lives in the
shadow of systemic racism,
"people of color and people who are not.
"So this is not an attack
on our police department"
is specifically what the mayor said.
He says he's not calling
out the South Bend Police.
He says he's calling,
he's saying that every city in America,
every mayor in America has to deal with
the issue of systemic
racism that does exist.
I mean, surely you would
agree that every city, mayor,
police department in America
should stand up to that.
- No ma'am I really don't
believe that's the issue.
The issue is not race at all
especially with this incident
color has absolutely nothing to do with.
Systemic is including everyone and--
- Systemic means common though.
And systemic racism is
an issue in the country.
- Well, the definition actually
of systemic actually says
the system, so that's what he's called for
and many of the comments he's made,
even the ones he just made
on Monday were backpedaling
from what he had mentioned before.
- Let me play for you, the
mayor was asked to respond
to your criticism yesterday
and to recuse himself
from the investigation.
Let me play for you his response.
- Well, first of all I don't
make disciplinary decisions
so I would expect them to understand
that this is a matter
for our Board of Safety
which is a board of civilians
that I appoint to take up
and I've been careful not
to weigh in on the incident
while the investigation is going on.
But one of the things I
really need to continue
conveying to our police officers
is that it is not anti-police
to be pro-racial justice.
On the contrary we absolutely can
and absolutely must be both.
- They mayor says the
investigation's being handled
by the Board of Safety.
What would removing himself
from the investigation actually do?
- If he continues to talk about it,
especially on a presidential campaign
it influences all of those
members on the Board of Safety
and those are handpicked by him,
members of the Board of
Safety so they would be
greatly influenced by any of his words
so he should not mention
this investigation at all
on his presidential campaign.
- Have you reached out to
the mayor to discuss this?
- Mayor Buttigieg has called me,
we have not had a dialogue
but we are willing
to have a dialogue.
It is needed.
He had ignored previous requests
before the shooting to speak with the FOP
on other issues.
- Well, I look forward
to hearing what comes
of that conversation, Sergeant.
We'll check back in with you.
Thank you for being here.
- Thank you.
- Coming up, "As you wish."
Remember that line?
It's one of the many classic,
and there are millions of
them basically from this movie
you can hear my bias in my voice now.
Millions of classic one
liners from the movie,
"The Princess Bride".
Cary Elwes who played Westley of course
joins us to talk about
the iconic '80s film
and the new CNN original
series, "The Movies".
We'll be right back.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Summer's not stopping
or slowing down.
So take advantage of all
of summer's opportunities
with our limited time
offers while you still can.
Hurry into the Acura
Summer of Performance Event
going on now.
Visit your local Acura dealer
to test drive the 2019 ILX.
Starting MSRP 25,900.
- [Announcer] Do your asthma
symptoms ever hold you back?
About 50% of people with severe asthma
have too many cells called,
eosinophils in their lungs.
Eosinophils are a key
cause of severe asthma.
Fasenra is designed to target
and remove these cells.
Fasenra is an add on
injection for people 12 and up
with asthma driven by eosinophils.
Fasenra is not a rescue medicine
or for other eosinophilic conditions.
Fasenra is proven to help
prevent severe asthma attacks,
improve breathing and can
lower oral steroid use.
Fasenra may cause allergic reactions.
Get help right away if you have swelling
of your face, mouth and
tongue or trouble breathing.
Don't stop your asthma treatments
unless your doctor tells you to.
Tell your doctor if you
have a parasitic infection
or your asthma worsens.
Headache and sore throat may occur.
Haven't you missed enough?
Ask an asthma specialist about Fasenra.
If you can't afford your
medication AstraZenica
may be able to help.
- In one week a lot will
happen in your life.
Wrinkles just won't.
Neutrogena Rapid Wrinkle Repair's
derm-proven retinol works so
fast it takes only one week
to reveal younger looking skin
making wrinkles look so last week.
Rapid Wrinkle Repair.
Pair with new Retinol Oil
for two tines the wrinkle fighting power.
Neutrogena.
("The More We Get Together")
(women laughing)
(little girl laughing)
- [Announcer] It's funny what happens
when people get together.
Holiday Inn, Holiday Inn Express.
We're there so you can be too.
- [Announcer] Do you have
a life insurance policy
you no longer need?
Now you can sell your
policy, even a term policy
for an immediate cash payment.
Call Coventry Direct to learn more.
- We thought we had planned
carefully for our retirement.
- But we quickly realized we needed a way
to supplement our income.
- Our friends sold their policy
to help pay their medical bills
and that got me thinking.
Maybe selling our policy could
help with our retirement.
- I was skeptical, so I did some research
and called Coventry Direct.
They explained life
insurance is a valuable asset
that can be sold.
- We learned that we can
sell all of our policy
or keep part of it with
no future payments.
Who knew?
We sold our policy.
Now we can relax and enjoy our
retirement as we had planned.
- [Announcer] If you have $100,000 or more
of life insurance you may
qualify to sell your policy.
Don't cancel or let your policy lapse
without finding out what its worth.
Visit CoventryDirect.com
to find out if your policy qualifies.
Or call 1-800-651-0200.
Coventry Direct, redefining insurance.
- [Announcer] The 2020 race is revving up.
Live from Detroit 20
candidates, two big nights.
The CNN Democratic Presidential Debates
July 30th and 31st only on CNN.
- [Announcer] Paid spokesperson.
- [Announcer] Attention,
this is a legal alert
for anyone who has used
RoundUp Weed Killer
and been diagnosed with
non-Hodgkin's lymphoma.
If you used RoundUp Weed
Killer and have been diagnosed
with non-Hodgkin's lymphoma
you may be entitled to
significant compensation.
A multimillion dollar
verdict was recently awarded
to a man whose non-Hodgkin's
lymphoma was linked
to RoundUp Weed Killer.
If you used RoundUp Weed Killer
and were diagnosed with
non-Hodgkin's lymphoma
you may be entitled to
significant compensation.
Call now.
♪ Limu Emu ♪
- [Announcer] And Doug.
- What do all these people
have in common, Limu?
(paper rustling)
Exactly, nothing.
They're completely different people.
That's why they make
customized car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay for what they need.
(change clattering)
Yes, and they could save a ton.
You've done it again, Limu.
(Limu squawks)
- [Announcer] Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty, Liberty, Liberty ♪
(upbeat music)
- This Sunday the all new CNN
original series, "The Movies"
takes you inside some of
the iconic American films
through the decades.
The movies that have
stirred our imagination,
influenced our culture, shaped our lives.
One of my favorites the 1980s
hit, "The Princess Bride".
- He didn't fall!
Inconceivable!
- You keep using that word.
I do not think it means
what you think it means.
- "The Princess Bride" is
a blend between romance,
satire, adventure, swashbuckling.
I mean it's all mixed in and
it's a very strange mixture
hard to capture.
- Westley, what about the ROUS's?
- Rodents of unusual size?
I don't think they exist.
(rodent growling)
- You have to walk a balance, you know?
It's a fine line between
stupid and clever.
- Beat it or I'll call the brut squad.
- I'm on the brute squad.
- You are the brute squad.
- Joining me right now is
actor, author, screenwriter
of course the man who
played the part of Westley
in the iconic movie, "The
Princess Bride" Cary Elwes.
Cary thank you so much for being here.
- It's my joy, Kate.
Thank you for having me.
- I can't even tell you how much fun,
how excited I was when
I found out I was able
to finally speak with
the one and only Westley
of, "The Princess Bride".
It really shows how iconic this movie is.
- Thank you so much, I
know I'm very blessed.
I call it the gift that keeps on giving.
- It sure does.
So, in taking the role,
the meaning, the legend,
the legacy of, "The Princess
Bride" in the context
of this CNN look into the movies
in this episode that we're looking at
I wanna read you how director Rob Reiner
describes, "The Princess Bride".
He describes it as
"A blend between romance, satire,
adventure, swashbuckling".
And he says, "I mean it's all mixed into
"a strange mixture
that's hard to capture".
It got me thinking when
this first came out in 1987
the studio didn't even
know how to market it.
Is it because it was
such a strange mixture
that made it such a classic do you think?
- I think that's part of it, Kate.
It was a hard film for them to market
because they couldn't figure out
which genre they should focus on.
Was it a romance film,
was it an adventure,
was it a fantasy, was it a comedy?
And they'd never seen a
film like that before.
In fact I don't think anyone had
so I mean Rob describes
it perfectly when he says
that he wanted us to just make sure
that we didn't play the lines for laughs.
- When did you first know that the film
had found its audience?
That it was so much, it was
so, it had such following.
- Well, you know it's interesting Kate.
It didn't have a big
following when it came out.
It came out the same time
as, "Fatal Attraction"
which just cleared out every other movie
that was competing with it.
- Slightly different
from, "Fatal Attraction."
- Slightly different genre
but again the poster that Fox
came up with was very unusual.
It didn't really sell the movie very well
and it was a very beautiful poster
but nobody knew what the film was.
Was it a kids movie, was it
a girls movie with the title
and it's only through word of mouth
it was really the college
campuses that students
that really picked up on the film.
And it wasn't until 10
years later when the film
came out on VHS that it had this,
it literally went from being mostly dead
to having a whole new life
and I'll never forget, I was in New York
and I was ordering a
hamburger or something
in a restaurant and the waitress said,
"How do you want that cooked?"
And I said, "Medium rare"
and she goes, "As you wish."
And that was the first time I'd heard it
being said by anyone.
And my life changed after that.
I forever people asking me on
the street to say that line.
- You wrote about the experience.
You wrote a memoir in 2014
about the making of the film.
Was it as much fun to
make as it was to watch.
- Well that's why I wrote the book, Kate.
'Cause fans always come up to me and say,
"Was it as much fun
making it as it looks?"
And I said it was more fun.
And I realized that that wasn't sufficient
to make them feel
satisfied and so I thought
well I should write a book about it
and share it with everyone
just how much fun it really was
and I think you can see it
translates onto the screen.
I can't remember a single
day without laughter.
- That's so good to hear
as someone who's such a fan
of the film.
There are so many one liners.
I was just kind of banting
them about with my producer
before we came to you.
Other than, "As you wish" what
are some of the other ones
that always stick in your head?
What would you say your favorites are?
- Oh my gosh, I love,
"Anybody want a peanut?"
which is just silly.
"Never get involved in a land
war in Asia" is pretty great.
- Do not forget, "My
name is Inigo Montoya.
"You killed my father, prepare to die."
- I mean, you know Paul
Mandy says he gets asked that
literally every five minutes.
It's incredible.
Wally Shawn said he can't walk
down the street in New York
without somebody saying,
"Inconceivable" to him.
If he drops his keys or misses a cab
or is late for an airplane,
you know somebody says it to him.
- I still try to drop
"Princess Bride" lines on TV
whenever humanly possible
probably much to the eye rolls
of my entire audience.
- That's hilarious, that's
hilarious, that's great to know.
- Thank you so much for being here
and sharing with us.
- My pleasure.
Thank you, Kate.
- [Kate] "The Movies" premiers
Sunday night, nine Eastern
and Pacific only on CNN.
Coming up next the acting
DHS Chief vows to take action
after a report reveals
a secret Facebook group
from border agents.
We'll be back.
- [Announcer] This is Anne Marie Pegils.
Her Saturdays are a never
ending montage of comfort.
- [Man] Where have you been all my life?
- [Announcer] But then Anne
laid on a Serta Perfect Sleeper
and realized her life was
only just sorta comfortable.
Not just sorta comfortable,
Serta comfortable.
- My insurance rates are
probably gonna double.
- But Dad you've got
- [Man] Allstate with accident forgiveness
that guarantee your rates won't go up
just because of an accident.
- Smart kid.
- [Man] Indeed.
Are you in good hands?
- Reality check everyone.
People look at your jawline.
- [Announcer] That's right, no one wants
a sagging jawline or double chin.
- As we get a little
older the jawline starts
to sag a little bit.
- I need a product that's
going to step in and help me.
- [Announcer] Now you can
just make them disappear.
Call now for introductory offer
on brand new Genucel Jawline Treatment.
Genucel Jawline Treatment
tightens, defines and contours
you saggy jawline in minutes.
- The first time I used Genucel
I was just astounded and amazed.
The immediate tightening effect that I saw
in my jowl line was just amazing.
- I saw results immediately
after using Genucel.
- I started using the
Genucel jawline product
and I was amazed at
the results I received.
- [Announcer] Watch
Genucel Jawline Treatment
tighten and define the appearance
of the skin around the jawline
and visibly reduce that
pesky double chin area.
Look at the amazing difference.
Genucel's new Jawline
Treatment with dual peptide
and MDL technology.
Chamonix's most advanced technology ever.
It not only tightens saggy jawline
but it plumps the lipophilic
layers of your skin
to contour and define the
jawline within minutes.
- Genucel works so well that my phone
didn't even recognize me.
I had to reset my face ID.
- I never thought I would
use any kind of product
on my face and when I
started using Genucel
I noticed a difference almost immediately
and I would recommend it to everybody.
- Try it, you will be amazed.
You will see an immediate effect
and you will not believe the results
that you see in the mirror.
- [Announcer] You'll see
a noticeable difference
and look years younger in minutes.
Plus the results get better every day.
Call or click now to order Genucel
brand new Jawline Treatment
absolutely risk free
and get a second month for half price.
Order now and you'll
also get the breakthrough
Genucel Immediate Effects
for results in minutes.
And this introductory offer is backed
by our ironclad, no questions asked 100%
money back guarantee.
Call or click now and upgrade
to free express shipping.
Go to Genucel.com now or call
the number on your screen.
That's Genucel.com, Genucel.com.
- [Announcer] When
redesigning the Honda HR-V LX
and new sport we thought
why not make them adaptable?
For big stuff and small stuff.
And why not nimble?
Tight corners kind of nimble.
And why not smart?
Not just street smart, tech smart?
And why not end with a
statement no one else can make?
The redesigned HR-V.
(upbeat music)
- The deli scene.
When we first did it Meg, rightfully,
was a little nervous about it.
You got crew members standing around.
- You okay?
- Rob says, "Here's what I want".
He proceeds to have an orgasm
that Mighty Joe Young would be jealous of.
- Yes, oh God, I'm pounding the table.
- Yes, yes!
- And I realize 'cause my
mother is sitting there
I'm having an orgasm
in front of my mother.
- I'll have what she's having.
- [Announcer] The movies we
love and the stories behind them
starts Sunday night on CNN.
- [Announcer] Not getting enough cash back
with that credit card?
Turn to the nerds.
Looking for the perfect mortgage?
Oops, sorry about that.
Easily compare credit cards, mortgages,
savings accounts and
more at NerdWallet.com.
- No wrong move!
Old fashioned bandages get dirty.
They can let in water and germs.
Look, it's falling off.
New Skin is the flexible liquid bandage
that seals out the bad stuff.
There's a spray too.
- [Announcer] New Skin,
rethink how you heal.
- [Announcer] Congratulations,
you're a writer.
But wait, you have to
actually publish your book.
Discover Publishers will help
you find the right publisher
to get your book in bookstores.
It's completely free.
- [Announcer] Go to FreeAuthorInfo.com
or call us at 800-251-4119.
- [Announcer] Men, wanna feel
younger, stronger, leaner?
You don't have to slow down after 40.
New Nugenix Total-T
is our most powerful man-boosting.