- [Narrator] And did they have
an impact on people's lives?
- One of the most important
bands to ever walk the Earth.
Their influence will never, ever go away.
- They had the perfect
combination with a classic lineup.
They had the personalities
that could create friction,
but created great music.
And they don't come along very often.
- It was just a giant firework display,
that was just the best you've ever seen.
But it wasn't built to last.
It exploded into the sky and we all went,
"Aah!", and it was gone, fabulous.
(foreboding ambient music)
(siren wails)
- We have a death.
We need to confirm identification,
and then we need to perform an autopsy.
- The lead singer of the rock
band, Nirvana, Kurt Cobain,
has died of a gunshot wound in Seattle.
- [Narrator] The world was
stunned when Kurt Cobain,
the 27-year old musician and
self-styled prince of grunge,
was found dead.
- Kurt Cobain was a genius,
he was the powerful voice of a generation.
- He was the true artist,
even in his pain he was genuine.
- [Narrator] But with
success came pressures,
that Kurt found hard to handle.
- He worked so hard to become
the millionaire rockstar,
and then once he did, he
didn't like it very much.
(glass smashes)
- [Narrator] And on April 8th, 1994,
when Kurt Cobain was found
dead at his Seattle mansion,
it appeared to be a
clear-cut case of suicide.
- Kurt was the poster boy for suicide.
I said he's going to kill himself.
- [Narrator] But despite
leaving a suicide note,
many people refused to
believe that Kurt Cobain
had taken his own life.
- I knew from the beginning
that Kurt had been murdered.
- Kurt Cobain's death
certificate says that he died
from a single shotgun wound to the head.
But why would a man who's just achieved
his lifelong goal of becoming a rockstar,
and starting a family, kill himself?
And could foul play have been involved?
(dramatic symphonic music)
(suspenseful music)
- [Narrator] Dr. Michael Hunter is
a world-renowned forensic pathologist,
and the chief medical examiner
in one of America's biggest cities.
He's performed over 4000 autopsies,
to investigate and reveal
the cause of death.
- Kurt Cobain's investigative
records show that he died
from a shotgun wound to the
head, fired through the mouth.
But why would a man who has
struggled to make it a musician,
and who'd just started
a family kill himself?
I'm gonna use all the available
evidence to investigate
what happened to Kurt both
mentally and physically,
and discover more about why he died.
(suspenseful music)
- [Narrator] April 1st, 1994, 2:30pm.
Four days before Kurt Cobain's death.
Kurt is at the Exodus Recovery
Center in Marina Del Rey.
He's trying to kick the heroin addiction
he's developed since becoming a rockstar.
- One of the people he smoked
a cigarette with outside,
said that Kurt just seemed
like a happy-go-lucky guy,
he didn't seem like he had
a problem in the world.
He seemed very excited about life.
- [Narrator] Kurt had only
recently become a millionaire,
after a lifetime of financial hardship,
and had just bought himself a mansion
in an exclusive area of Seattle,
where he lived with his
wife, Courtney Love,
and his 19-month old baby, Frances Bean.
In a recently discovered interview,
recorded a few months before his death,
Kurt claimed he'd never been happier.
- [Kurt's Voice] Ever
since I've been married
and I've had a child,
within the last year,
everything, my whole mental
state and my physical state
has been, it's just almost improved 100%.
I've never been more optimistic.
- But within five days of appearing
optimistic about the future,
Kurt Cobain was dead.
He was 27, and he joins
a long list of stars
who died at this age.
Including Jim Morrison, Jimi
Hendrix, and Amy Winehouse.
It's an exclusive club,
and I want to find out
what led Kurt to doing it.
(bright ambient music)
- [Narrator] Kurt Donald Cobain,
was born on February
20th, 1967, in Aberdeen,
a small industrial town located
two hours south of Seattle.
- Aberdeen was a logging town
where everybody was macho.
He certainly wasn't the
type who was gonna go out
and cut down trees.
- [Narrator] Kurt's dad was a mechanic,
and his mother was a waitress,
but his upbringing was far from easy.
- The whole Cobain
family was dysfunctional.
I'm talking all of us.
- Where you going tonight?
- Oh, working late.
- The dysfunctional part I think
was that he was living with
parents who were using
more alcohol than normal.
(parents arguing)
(rising symphonic music)
And it's hard for you to
be a happy little kid,
if you're growing up in
a family that's fighting
and don't really know
how to raise children.
- [Kurt's Voice] I was
ashamed of my parents.
I couldn't face some of
my friends at school,
because I desperately wanted to have
the classic typical
family, mother, father,
I wanted that security.
(young Kurt playing guitar)
- [Narrator] Kurt's parents
separated when he was nine.
He found solace in music,
which he showed promise
at from an early age.
- He was a child prodigy
who possessed this rare,
unique artistic talent.
- Music saved Kurt,
I think it was the only way he
knew to express his feelings.
And I really do think it
was therapeutic for him.
- [Narrator] Kurt started
by playing the drums
before moving on to guitar.
(deep music)
But it wasn't until he was 18,
that he met Krist Novoselic,
and formed the band, Nirvana.
It was Kurt's approach that
would be at the forefront
of a new style of music.
- How he was able to take punk music,
old rock and roll,
minimalist melodic music,
stick it all in a soup,
and come out with what he came out with,
I think that was pretty revolutionary.
- [Narrator] This fusion of rock and punk,
became known as grunge.
It is epitomized in their iconic track,
"Smells Like Teen Spirit".
♪ With the lights out
it's less dangerous ♪
♪ Here we are now entertain us ♪
♪ I feel stupid and contagious ♪
♪ A mulatto ♪
Nirvana's album, Nevermind,
released in 1991,
went to the top of the
charts around the world,
and established Kurt Cobain
as the biggest rockstar of his generation.
In February 1992, Kurt
married the former stripper
and lead singer of the
band, Hole, Courtney Love.
- As soon as she married him,
I listened to a lot of his poetry,
and a lot of his music and I thought,
well this guy's pretty profound.
- I think he was popular
because he was wounded,
he looked like a person who
was down on his luck and rebellious.
Yeah so I think the kids
could really relate to that.
- He spoke to this lost generation,
and became the voice of the generation.
(light ambient music)
- This is a photograph of Nirvana,
taken six months prior
to Kurt Cobain's death,
and I'm surprised at how small Kurt is.
Bass guitarist, Krist Novoselic,
is incredibly tall, at
six foot six inches.
And drummer David Grohl, is six feet tall.
According to his records,
Kurt was five nine,
but looked considerably smaller.
This could be due to a disorder
that he was suffering from,
called scoliosis, and in this
recently discovered interview,
Kurt sheds new light on what
he thought caused this condition.
- [Kurt's Voice] I had scoliosis
when I was in junior high,
and I've been playing guitar ever since,
and the weight of the guitar has made
my back grow in this curvature,
so when I stand, you know,
everything's sideways.
(suspenseful music)
- [Dr. Hunter] Scoliosis,
or curvature of the spine,
occurs in about 3% of people,
and most commonly arises
in the teenage years.
The curve is usually either
S-shaped with two bends,
or C-shaped with one.
- His music felt like
he was always in pain,
that he was angst-ridden,
and that's a typical
reflection of the scoliosis
that he battled with.
- It's a common misconception
that scoliosis causes pain,
but that is not always the case,
and the cause is oftentimes unknown.
This is an x-ray of Kurt Cobain's spine,
and it shows that he
has C-shaped scoliosis.
This wouldn't be caused by
the weight of his guitar,
but it could be exacerbated by it.
(dramatic symphonic music)
As there is no mention of any pain,
or psychological distress
associated with this condition,
I don't believe that this is
responsible for his death.
However, Kurt did suffer from another
long-standing medical condition,
that had a huge impact on him.
So I want to investigate whether
it led him to take his own life.
(light piano music)
- I remember putting on a brave face
to hide my symptoms of depression.
I was on an anti-depressant,
but I still had depression symptoms.
It was tough getting through the day,
hiding how I really felt.
Something had to change.
So I talked to my doctor for real,
no more saying, "Oh, I'm fine".
This time, I spoke up about
living behind the mask,
and he told me about Rexulti.
He said that Rexulti, when
added to an anti-depressant,
has been proven to help
reduce symptoms of depression,
without giving up the
progress I may have made
on my anti-depressant.
- [Narrator] Rexulti is not for everyone.
Call your doctor about
unusual changes in behavior,
worsening depression,
or thoughts of suicide.
Anti-depressants can increase
these in those 24 and younger.
Elderly dementia patients taking Rexulti
have an increased risk of death or stroke.
Call your doctor if you have high fever,
stiff muscles and confusion,
to address a possible
life-threatening condition,
or if you have uncontrollable
muscle movements,
as these may be permanent.
Rexulti has been shown to increase
blood sugar in some people.
Other risks are increased
cholesterol, weight gain,
unusual urges or compulsive behaviors,
decreased white blood
cells, which can be serious,
dizziness on standing,
seizures, trouble swallowing,
and impaired judgment or motor skills.
- It was time to make a change.
That's why I asked my
doctor about adding Rexulti.
- [Narrator] Feel better
about facing the world.
Pay $0 for your first
Rexulti prescription,
details at Rexulti.com.
- [Narrator] When you carry out large
three topping pizzas for 7.99,
Domino's Carryout
Insurance has you covered.
Cos stuff happens.
(man's foot squeaks against banana)
(funky music)
Stuff like this.
(skunk chatters)
(man yells)
Just bring it back and
we'll remake it for free.
- [Breathy Female Voice] Air Wick.
- [Narrator] You don't live in one corner,
fragrance shouldn't either.
Air Wick's new technology releases
fragrance upwards and
outwards, unlike Febreze.
So now you can fill every
corner with fragrance.
Upgrade to Air Wick.
(lively rock music)
- [Narrator] Protect your
pet with the number one name
in flea and tick protection.
Frontline Plus, trusted by
vets for nearly 20 years.
- I used to run low on
cash right before payday,
and not be able to do anything.
But now that I'm banking with Chime,
I get paid up to two days
early with direct deposit.
I've just got paid.
(dog barks)
Start banking with Chime
today, at chime.com.
- This is nice.
- Yeah.
Yeah, this is nice.
- Mm, how did you make the
dip so rich and creamy?
- Oh it's a Philadel--
- Family recipe.
- Can I see it?
- No.
- [Narrator] Philadelphia Dips,
so good you'll take all the credit.
("I Don't Wanna Miss
A Thing" by Aerosmith)
♪ I don't wanna close my eyes ♪
♪ I don't wanna fall asleep ♪
♪ Cos I miss you baby ♪
♪ And I don't wanna miss a thing ♪
(upbeat music)
- Oof!
- Arm & Hammer plus Oxi Clean
with Odor Blasters detergent.
It eliminates tough odors
and blasts away the oof,
for a clean that will leave you in--
- Ah!
- At a fraction of the cost,
in packs and liquid.
Arm & Hammer, more power to you.
- [Narrator] What makes
DiGiornio crispy pan pizza
different than delivery?
♪ Pan pan pan pan pan pan pan pan ♪
- [Narrator] You bake
it fresh in its own pan,
giving our DiGiorno pizza
a crispy caramelized crust.
♪ Pan pan pan ♪
It's not delivery, it's DiGiorno.
- Hi, I'm Mike Siegel for Reelz.
Want a great movie you can watch at home?
Reelz recommends,
"Fighting With My Family."
Dwayne Johnson helps an oddball teen
with pro-wrestling
dreams hit the big time.
Watch "Fighting With
My Family", on demand.
And tomorrow night on Reelz, don't miss,
"Paul Walker Collision Course",
followed by Dale Earnhardt,
then "Hulk Hogan Fortune Fight",
it's all tomorrow night seven
Eastern and Pacific, on Reelz.
(suspenseful electronic music)
- A member of the rock
music scene is dead.
Police in Seattle say that Kurt Cobain,
the lead singer of the group, Nirvana,
has taken his own life.
- [Narrator] April 8th, 1994.
Kurt Cobain is found dead
at his house in Seattle,
with a gunshot wound to his head.
(suspenseful music)
Expert coroner and forensic
pathologist, Dr. Michael Hunter,
is examining all the
medical evidence available,
to try and work out if and why
Kurt Cobain took his own life.
- Suicides are rarely
down to just one factor.
They're oftentimes a mixture of both
physical and psychological conditions.
So I want to dig deeper to find out
what precipitated his death.
(light symphonic music)
- [Narrator] March 3rd, 1994, 11:30pm.
The Excelsior Hotel, Rome.
One month before Kurt Cobain's death.
Kurt has arrived in Rome to
meet his wife, Courtney Love.
He's just pulled out of
Nirvana's European tour,
blaming it on bronchitis.
Kurt's relationship with
Courtney is also suffering,
with rumors of divorce.
But despite their problems,
they leave their daughter
Frances Bean with their nanny,
and spend the evening
drinking champagne together.
- [Courtney] You need to
do what you need to do.
- Champagne's a very un-Kurtlike drink.
He wasn't really a big
drinker at the best of times.
Champagne is more of a rockstar drink,
and he wasn't into that.
- Excuse me?
- The couple drink
into the early hours
before they fall asleep.
(soft rock music)
(skies thundering)
At 6:25am, Courtney wakes to find Kurt
is no longer beside her.
(clock ticks)
(foreboding music)
- Kurt?
Kurt, come on wake up.
I said wake up!
- When she fails to wake him,
she calls for help.
(Courtney dialing phone)
- Hello?
(dramatic music)
Yeah, I need an ambulance.
(paramedic knocks on door)
- [Narrator] At 6:40am,
a paramedic arrives.
When he also fails to revive Kurt,
he's taken to the Umberto I hospital,
less than two miles away.
- I listened to the news,
and they said that Courtney
had found Kurt unconscious,
and blue, which to me means,
that's like the color of death.
I just thought this guy is
a poster boy for suicide.
I went to his grandfather, Leland,
and I told him I was really,
really worried about Kurt.
I said you've got to talk to him,
he's going to kill himself.
(nervy music)
- [Narrator] It was later revealed that
Kurt had left a suicide note.
He had admitted in many
interviews to using heroin,
but had in fact overdosed on Rohypnol.
- Rohypnol is a tranquilizer,
also known as the "Date-Rape Drug",
but it's also prescribed
to treat heroin withdrawal.
A month later, Kurt was dead,
leaving little clue if and
why he took his own life.
But in a note found at
the scene, Kurt mentions,
and I quote, his burning nauseous stomach,
and this is a reference to
the chronic stomach pain,
that was so debilitating that
he said it blighted his life.
So could this be the reason
that he attempted suicide in Rome,
and finally took his life a month later?
(ambient piano music)
- [Narrator] Kurt's parents' marriage,
started to collapse when Kurt was seven.
By the time he was
nine, and they divorced,
their breakup was having a
devastating effect on him.
- When his parents split,
he started to change.
Because for any kid, it's not easy.
And that's sort of when the
stomach pain first surfaced.
- He had stomach problems
from an early age,
and it wasn't diagnosed.
- If you look at any of the sort of
the seminal moments in his life,
that stomach pain was there.
It may very well have been that
part of his condition was psychosomatic,
we know that being in emotional turmoil,
makes physical pain feel worse.
So it wouldn't be shocking to assume that
his mental state did
affect his physical state.
- It haunted him because he
couldn't function properly,
in everyday life.
(rising string music)
He really felt that unless he
got rid of the stomach pain,
basically life was over.
- I can see from Kurt's records,
that he was treated for
his stomach condition,
and he also had three
endoscopic procedures,
to try to determine precisely
the cause of his pain.
An endoscopy is where a
small camera is inserted
through the mouth and then
moved down the throat,
into the esophagus, stomach,
and upper-gastrointestinal tract.
The camera relays the
images back to the screen,
where the doctor can see inside
the body in great detail.
- [Narrator] But despite having
three endoscopic examinations,
the doctors could find no explanation
for Kurt's chronic stomach pain,
leading him to speculate on its causes.
- [Kurt's Voice] The reason
I've gotta endoscope,
they find a red irritation in my stomach,
it's just psychosomatic, that's all,
from anger and screaming,
I mean my mom had it when
she was in her early 20's,
for a few years and it
just eventually went away.
She was in the hospital
all the time because of it.
(fast-paced music)
- Stomach pain obviously
ran in the Cobain family.
But in Kurt's case it's
because of his scoliosis.
This condition can pinch abdominal nerves,
causing severe stomach pain.
In 1993, when it was discovered that this
was the reason for his abdominal pain,
a simple prescription appears to have
brought the condition under control.
So, I don't believe that this
is responsible for his death.
Kurt was a frequent heroin user,
and claimed that he took it
to treat his abdominal pain.
So I wanna investigate what role
this drug played in his death.
- [Narrator] Smashing Pumpkins.
- D'arcy and Billy were shouting
at each other all the time.
- In a lot of ways I mean this is like,
the completion of everything,
what was started is over.
- [Narrator] Breaking the
Band, all new next on Reelz.
- [Narrator] Saddle up,
the Rodeo King is now
part of the King's Collection.
Two flame-grilled patties,
melted American cheese,
stacked with bacon, onion
rings and barbecue sauce,
crafted by hand, grilled by flame.
It's the Rodeo King, only at Burger King.
- And we'll see you in five.
(playful piano music)
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
(taps bottle)
What are you, what are you doing?
What are you doing, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
♪ Oh it's your thing ♪
♪ Do what you wanna do ♪
- [Narrator] Dogs have evolved,
but their nutritional
needs remain instinctual.
That's why there's
Purina One True Instinct,
high protein for strong muscles.
A different breed of natural nutrition,
Purina One True Instinct,
also in grain-free for dog and cats.
- So nice to meet you, June, Jane,
G, Kay, Raj and Ray!
- [Narrator] Good job, brain!
Say hello to Neuriva, a
new brain supplement with
clinically proven
ingredients that fuel five
indicators of brain performance, Neuriva.
- [Narrator] Parodontax
Complete Protection.
If you see traces of blood
when you brush or floss,
which kind of toothpaste do you choose?
One for healthy gums,
or one for strong teeth?
You don't have to choose.
Complete Protection from Parodontax,
has eight designed
benefits for healthy gums,
and strong teeth.
Take control, and leave
bleeding gums behind,
with Complete Protection from Parodontax.
♪ Take your time ♪
♪ Build a home ♪
♪ Build a place where we all can belong ♪
- [Narrator] Give Extra, get Extra,
with new Extra Refreshers gum.
(soft rock music)
- [Narrator] When you
get right down to it,
freedom is the ability
to go where you wanna go,
and do what you wanna do.
So, what do you wanna do?
The 2019 Jeep Compass.
Hurry into the 4th of July Sales Event,
and get $500 additional
bonus cash on select models,
visit Jeep.com.
- I used to run low on
cash right before payday,
and not be able to do anything.
See, I'm not doing anything.
But now that I'm banking
with Chime I get paid
up to two days early with direct deposit.
I just got paid.
(dog barks)
Plus, Chime helps me grow
may savings automatically,
and unlike the place I used to bank,
it doesn't charge me
a bunch of crazy fees.
I'd be crazy to go back.
Start banking with Chime
today, at chime.com.
- [Narrator] Are you a
sunrise cycle snacker?
An afternoon multi-tasker snacker?
Or a midnight movie
attacker watcher snacker?
Whatever type of snacker you are,
Sargento Balanced Breaks are
a perfectly balanced snack,
any time of day, made with natural cheese,
and other delicious ingredients.
So even if you're a tarmac snacker,
a balanced six-pack snacker,
a backpack packer snacker,
or a lumberjack on horseback,
in a cul-de-sac snacker.
Sargento Balanced Breaks
are the snack for you.
- Sargento.
- We're real cheese people.
- [Narrator] Breaking the
Band, Smashing Pumpkins,
next on Reelz.
(suspenseful music)
- [Narrator] Expert coroner
and forensic pathologist,
Dr. Michael Hunter, is
examining all the available
medical evidence about the
death of the musical icon
and prince of grunge, Kurt Cobain.
He was found dead in his Seattle mansion,
with a gunshot wound to his head.
For over 20 years, controversy
has surrounded his death,
with many refusing to
believe it was suicide.
Now Dr. Hunter plans to
finally get to the bottom
of what really killed Kurt Cobain.
- When Kurt returned from
Rome, his heroin use increased.
He was using about $400
worth of heroin every day,
and that's $700 in today's prices.
This is an enormous amount of heroin
to take on a daily basis,
and those who were close to him realized,
that if they didn't do something,
Kurt was going to die.
(light piano music)
(helicopter whirs)
- [Narrator] March 25th, 1994,
11:15am, Seattle, Washington,
10 days before Kurt Cobain's death.
Kurt walks into his living room,
having just injected heroin.
- What's this?
- And gets a surprise.
- We need a change.
- Change?
- An intervention was organized
by his entertainment
attorney, Rosemary Carroll,
and her husband, Danny Goldberg,
several of his closest people were there,
including his best friends.
- We care about you, dude.
- They thought Kurt was in a dark zone,
they thought he was doing too much heroin.
(rising music)
(Kurt argues)
- [Narrator] But the
intervention backfires.
With Kurt accusing his
friends of being hypocrites,
for also using drugs while
telling him to stop taking them.
- Yeah it is, no we do drugs,
we play guitar, we play--
- I'm not talking about a bit
of party coke I'm talking about
life and death, all right?
I'm taking about a baby, yes.
- Tell me I'm wrong.
- It's pretty hard,
for somebody to tell a drug-user,
that they shouldn't be using it.
Because that's where
they find their peace.
And I'm sure he did
not want to stop using,
and that's one of the reasons
he got angry about it.
You know, "Don't tell me what to do".
- This isn't fun anymore.
- [Narrator] By now Kurt's
excessive drug taking
has not only alienated all of his friends,
but his marriage to Courtney
is also on the rocks.
- Hypocrites, hypocrites, hypocrites!
Every single one of you, damn it!
(Kurt slams door)
- I believe that Kurt's adverse
reaction to the intervention
is because he didn't see
himself as a drug addict.
He claims he was using
heroin not for enjoyment,
but for medicinal reasons.
- [Kurt's Voice] I've had this
stomach condition for years,
and there were times
especially during touring,
and while off the tour where I
just felt like a drug addict,
because I was starving,
and I went to all these different doctors,
and they couldn't find out
what was wrong with me,
and I tried everything.
Nothing worked and I just decided that
if I'm going to feel like
a junkie every morning,
and be vomiting every day
then I may as well, you know,
take a substance that kills that pain.
- Kurt initially got into heroin,
because it seemed to
him to be a painkiller.
His whole teenage years he was looking
for various pills and prescriptions,
to help get over his bad
back, his bad stomach.
- I think the idea of
taking a drug to escape pain
is something that one hears very often.
And while that is kind of,
I guess understandable in the short term,
it doesn't negate the fact
that it's still a choice.
And the excuse of,
well I had no choice
because I was in pain,
is one that again, you hear
a lot of addicts using.
(foreboding music)
- Kurt's explanation that he used heroin
for pain relief may be true.
But the damage that that drug caused
far outweighed any conceived benefit.
But I found something
else in Kurt's background,
that might also explain his
reliance on chemical stimulants.
(ambient piano music)
(young Kurt drumming)
- [Narrator] In 1974, aged seven,
Kurt's manic behavior worried
his parents to such an extent,
that he is taken to the
doctor's where he's diagnosed
with attention deficit
hyperactivity disorder, or ADHD,
and prescribed the drug, Ritalin.
- Here you had an artistic kid,
who's a little bit
different to begin with,
and wants to rather draw than do his math,
and that sort of thing.
He may be acting out a bit
because of his home life,
so they did put him on Ritalin.
- Ritalin is the common name
for the drug, methylphenidate.
And it's classified by the Drug
Enforcement Administration,
as a schedule two drug, in the
same classification as say,
cocaine, morphine, and amphetamines.
Ritalin works by increasing the activity
of the chemicals dopamine,
and noradrenaline,
in areas of the brain that play a part
in controlling attention and behavior.
- He was first prescribed Ritalin,
and you can see that
that might have started
a lifetime habit of
relying on various drugs
to balance his mood out.
Along with the Ritalin
there came sleeping pills,
because he couldn't
sometimes go to bed at night,
even as a youngster, so
already you can begin to see,
where there's a certain
amount of chemical assistance
going on just to get him through the day.
- [Narrator] After his parents' divorce,
Kurt stayed with each of them,
but following continual arguments
both asked him to leave.
At 15 years old, Kurt Cobain was homeless,
and his ADHD was going untreated.
Over the next four years
Kurt had 10 different homes,
he would stay at friends'
houses and sleep in hallways,
abandoned properties, or under a bridge.
As Kurt increasingly
dropped out of society,
he had run-ins with the law,
and was arrested for vandalism.
For a decade, his ADHD went untreated,
and his addiction to heroin
reached dangerous levels.
(dramatic percussive music)
- There is no evidence to suggest that
Ritalin itself leads to addiction.
But, children with ADHD
are two to three times
more likely to have substance
abuse issues later in life.
But after a lifetime of
relying on drugs to treat pain,
and to alter his moods,
Kurt finally agrees to seek treatment
for his addiction to heroin.
(suspenseful music)
- [Narrator] April 1st, 1994, 4:30pm.
Four days before Kurt Cobain's death.
Kurt has been at the Exodus
Recovery Center for 24 hours.
But despite his promise to
seek help for his addiction,
he decides he doesn't want to
continue with the treatment.
- The problem with the Exodus Center
is there's no physical constraint
to keep the person there
if he doesn't want to be there.
- Kurt climbed over a wall
because he missed his daughter,
several of his close friends,
he felt it was the time to restart life.
- [Narrator] But Kurt's cousin, Beverly,
thinks he fled rehab for
very different reasons.
There was a chance that he
could have been really helped
in that facility but he
apparently did not want
to stop using heroin.
(suspenseful music)
- It may very well have
been that the prospect
of coming off heroin was scary for Kurt.
You know, this was one
of his coping mechanisms.
This was one of the tools that
helped get him through the day,
in his mind this was one of the tools,
that kept the pain away,
that helped the creativity,
that kept him stable in some ways.
So I think one of the biggest barriers
to him actually seeking
the help that he did,
may have been this fear
of what it was like
to live without the heroin.
(fast-paced music)
- I can see from the report
that drug paraphernalia
was found at the scene of Kurt's death.
He also had a blood morphine level
of 1.52 milligrams per liter,
and that is a tremendous amount.
So the question I have
is what happened to Kurt,
from the time that he left rehab,
and when he died four days later?
(nervy percussive music)
- [Narrator] April 3rd, 1994, 2:21pm,
the Peninsula Hotel, Beverly Hills.
Two days before Kurt Cobain's death.
- Would you like to slow down?
- Well, my husband's gone missing.
- [Narrator] Private detective,
Tom Grant and his assistant,
are summoned by Kurt's wife, Courtney.
She tells him Kurt has fled
rehab and bought a shotgun,
and could be suicidal.
- Really, really strange recently and--
- Tom Grant was briefed to check around
for Kurt's whereabouts.
He was meant to go to the house
in Seattle, and find Kurt.
- [Narrator] April 7th, 1994, 2:45am.
- Kurt?
- Six days after
Kurt went missing--
- Hello?
- [Narrator] Private
investigator, Tom Grant,
searches his Seattle mansion,
but doesn't find him.
- Kurt?
(percussive music)
- [Narrator] April 8th, 8:40am,
seven days after Kurt's
disappearance from rehab,
an electrician is
installing security lights
on the building above Kurt's garage.
- The private eye and the
others, the Seattle police,
had not thought to check
that particular building,
but Gary Smith, the
electrician went up there,
and he saw Kurt's body lying on the floor.
(fast-paced music)
- [Narrator] The electrician
calls the police.
At 9:00am, paramedic John
Fisk arrives at the property.
- When we arrived at the scene,
we did not know whose house it was.
We were directed by the police
officer up around the garage.
I was probably the first
one to arrive at the door,
we could see a body laying inside,
with a gun evident in his lap.
I don't believe we could tell
whether it had just happened,
if he could still be alive.
I told the police officer we needed
to get in there right away,
indicating to him that I hoped
he would perform some forcible entry.
He felt that they needed
to wait for a supervisor,
we felt we didn't have the time.
(glass smashes)
(door closes)
As we entered the room
and approached the body,
it was evident that he was dead,
and there was nothing we could do for him.
It would appear that he had
been sitting on the floor
with his legs out and a
shotgun in between his legs,
and activated the trigger perhaps
with his thumb or something.
The wound was in his mouth,
and an exit wound to the
back-left side of his head.
His face wasn't badly
distorted or misshapen
like we often see with a
gunshot wound to the head.
(light ambient music)
- We are working on a
presumptive identification,
but until we confirm
and notify the family,
we will not release the name.
- The phone rang and it
was a newspaper reporter,
and he told me that
somebody had killed themself
in Kurt's garage.
And I said,
"Well, it can't be Kurt
because he's in treatment."
And he said, "No, no, he
left there a few days ago."
I sort of put two and two together,
and I went to my knees and sobbed.
(melancholy piano music)
- [Reporter] Kurt Cobain's
body was found inside
a garage apartment adjacent
to his Seattle home,
dead of an apparently
self-inflicted shotgun wound.
- It came on the radio,
and I was really depressed.
You know, it immediately makes
you remember that person,
that tugged my arm at the show and said,
"Hey, how you doing?",
just this cute little guy, you know?
Plus I was really enjoying
his music and imagining
how far he could take it.
- A post-mortem confirmed that Kurt Cobain
died from a single shot to the head,
by a 20-gauge Remington shotgun,
that he purchased only
eight days before he died.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Kurt's body was found
to the left of the
greenhouse, on it's back,
with a shotgun laying on his chest.
The barrel had been placed in his mouth,
and the trigger pulled,
discharging hundreds of
small lead shot through
the roof of his mouth, and into his brain.
The damage was catastrophic.
- The single shot fired
in Kurt Cobain's mouth,
would have killed him instantly.
And given the fact that
there's a suicide note,
this appears to be an open and shut case.
- [Narrator] But since the death,
many have refused to
accept it was a suicide,
and believe Kurt was murdered.
They claim to have irrefutable evidence
that this is the case.
So could Kurt Cobain have
really been murdered?
And if so, by whom?
(funky guitar music)
- [Narrator] Protect your
pet with the number one name
in flea and tick protection.
Frontline Plus, trusted by
vets for nearly 20 years.
- [Narrator] If your dishwasher doesn't
get dishes completely dry,
try Finish Jet Dry's new stronger formula.
It dries 100% better than
detergent alone, even plastics.
Get dishes drier than you
ever thought possible,
try Finish Jet Dry.
- [Narrator] At Domino's,
delivery is kind of our thing.
We even made a car for it,
so when you get pizza,
stuffed cheesy bread,
or any of the other mix and match items
delivered for just $5.99 each,
you can trust we'll do our
thing to get you your things,
because we know a thing or two
about delivery at Domino's.
- I can't tell you who I
am or what I witnessed,
but I can tell you Liberty Mutual
customized my car insurance
so I only pay for what I need.
(camera clicks)
- No, no, no, no, no!
- [Narrator] Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty liberty liberty liberty. ♪
- These new Vitafusion
Gummy Vitamins are organic?
Like farmer's market organic?
Like baby goats in totes organic?
Want to know what else
is organic, farmers?
New organic Gummy Vitamins from
Vitafusion, vitamin better.
- I used to run low on
cash right before payday
and not be able to do anything.
See, I'm not doing anything.
But, now that I'm banking
with Chime I get paid
up to two days early with direct deposit.
I just got paid.
(dog barks)
Plus, Chime helps me grow
my savings automatically,
and unlike the place I used to bank,
it doesn't charge me
a bunch of crazy fees.
I'd be crazy to go back.
- [Narrator] Start banking
with Chime today, at chime.com.
- [Narrator] How did we
test our Dixie Ultra plates?
With two pounds of steak, in each hand.
Dixie Ultra, stress-tested so
you can stress less at dinner.
(dramatic music)
- Hey come on, man!
- What, we said pantyhose, right?
- Here, eat this, creamy Snickers.
You could use a little smoothness.
(woman shouting)
(police sirens wail)
- [Narrator] Get smooth with
the fresh-ground nut butters
in new creamy Snickers.
- Dating at my age?
People say it's the perfect time,
but where would I even begin?
- [Narrator] Open laptop,
go to OurTime.com,
just take a look.
It's easy to take a look, on OurTime.
The dating site for people over 50.
- This is why we no
longer have to worry about
flushing too much toilet paper.
Rid-X contains billions of
enzymes proven to break down
even paper to help keep your
whole septic system healthy.
- [Narrator] Rid-X, the
number one septic brand,
also from Rid-X, try new RV Odor Control.
- [Narrator] What makes
DiGiorno crispy pan pizza
different than delivery?
♪ Pan pan pan pan pan pan pan pan ♪
- [Narrator] You bake
it fresh in its own pan,
giving our DiGiorno pizza
a crispy caramelized crust.
♪ Pan pan pan ♪
It's not delivery, it's DiGiorno.
(melancholy piano music)
- I've been saying I'm fine,
but really I'm struggling
to keep up this brave face,
to hide my symptoms of depression.
I'm taking my anti-depressant
like we discussed,
but I'm still feeling depressed.
Is it just me?
- It's not just you.
(stirring symphonic music)
Two out of three people
on anti-depressants,
may still experience symptoms.
When added to an anti-depressant,
Rexulti has been proven to help
reduce symptoms of depression.
- So I can stay on my
current anti-depressant,
and help build on the progress I've made.
Hey guys.
- Hey, hey!
- [Narrator] Rexulti is not for everyone.
Call your doctor about
unusual changes in behavior,
worsening depression
or thoughts of suicide.
Anti-depressants can increase
these in those 24 and younger.
Elderly dementia patients taking Rexulti
have an increased risk of death or stroke.
Call your doctor if you have high fever,
stiff muscles and confusion,
to address a possible
life-threatening condition,
or if you have uncontrollable
muscle movements,
as these may be permanent.
Rexulti has been shown to increase
blood sugar in some people.
Other risks are increased
cholesterol, weight gain,
unusual urges or compulsive behaviors,
decreased white blood
cells, which can be serious,
dizziness on standing,
seizures, trouble swallowing,
and impaired judgment or motor skills.
- Now I'm glad I talked with
my doctor about adding Rexulti.
- [Narrator] Feel better
about facing the world.
Pay $0 for your first
Rexulti prescription.
Details at Rexulti.com.
- Hi I'm Mike Siegel for Reelz.
Want a great movie you can watch at home?
Reelz recommends,
"Fighting With My Family".
Dwayne Johnson helps an oddball teen
with pro-wrestling
dreams hit the big time.
Watch "Fighting With
My Family", on demand.
And tomorrow night on Reelz,
don't miss "Paul Walker Collision Course",
followed by Dale Earnhardt,
then "Hulk Hogan Fortune Fight",
it's all tomorrow night, seven
Eastern and Pacific on Reelz.
(sparse piano music)
- [Narrator] Kurt Cobain's
sudden death at the age of 27,
sent shockwaves around the world.
The official verdict was that
he died as a result of suicide
from a gunshot wound to the head.
(brooding percussive music)
But this verdict has been
challenged by those who
don't believe Kurt Cobain's
death was a suicide.
Now, Dr. Michael Hunter plans to uncover
what really happened in
Kurt Cobain's final hours,
to reveal the true cause of his death.
(suspenseful music)
- Kurt Cobain's body lay undiscovered
for three days following his death.
And the autopsy revealed presence of
1.52 milligrams per liter
of morphine in the blood.
In the body, heroin
breaks down into morphine,
and this is an incredibly high level.
So some have argued that it is so high,
it would have been impossible
for Kurt to have the time
to shoot himself before passing out,
therefore foul play
must have been involved.
- [Narrator] One person who
believed that Kurt was murdered,
was the family member he was closest to,
his grandfather, Leland.
- He had so much dope in him that
he couldn't have possibly
brought that shotgun up.
And that's why I think he was murdered.
- [Narrator] Courtney
Love's estranged father
also believes Kurt was killed.
- I knew from the beginning,
maybe six months into it,
that Kurt had been murdered.
(deep electronic music)
The little box that he had
had Mexican tar heroin in it.
You can't shoot up enough
Mexican tar heroin,
to get that much heroin
in your bloodstream.
All the junkies I've talked to said,
"Oh no, that's absolutely impossible."
- [Narrator] More surprisingly,
Hank Harrison believes
his daughter could be
implicated in the murder.
He's had a tumultuous
relationship with Courtney
since his divorce from her mother,
and believes she had a
motive to want Kurt dead.
- There was a prenup,
and she was only gonna get
a small amount of money,
and Kurt had already asked for a divorce,
and a change in the will.
- [Narrator] Investigative
journalist, Ian Halperin,
has been following the story
for more than 20 years.
- If Kurt died, she would
inherit the whole Cobain estate,
to the tune of a hundred million dollars.
And if they would have divorced,
she would have walked away with nothing
because of the prenup.
(sparse ambient music)
- [Narrator] He also believes
that it would be impossible
for Kurt to shoot himself,
with such a high level
of heroin in his system,
and argues that there are other
highly suspicious inconsistencies,
surrounding Kurt Cobain's death.
(fast-paced music)
- Kurt's body was found
lying with the shotgun,
whomever killed him had gloves on.
There were no latent
fingerprints found on the gun.
Dead men don't wipe their own prints.
- [Narrator] It's also argued
there are inconsistencies
in the handwriting on the suicide note.
- I hired the two top
handwriting experts in the world,
to study the suicide
note and to dissect it,
and they said it was written
in two different handwritings.
The top of the note was
written in Kurt's handwriting,
and the bottom of the
note, the last five lines,
which dealt with the suicide,
was written in the
handwriting of somebody else.
(brooding electronic music)
- [Narrator] And those that
believe Kurt was killed,
think this is how it happened.
- Kurt was assassinated but
he didn't die all at once.
Whoever killed him did it in stages.
First thing you do is
incapacitate the person,
after he was knocked out with Rohypnol,
he got shot up with what we think to be
a massive dose of fentanyl.
He died, they had to give him a shotgun,
and shoot him to make it look like it was
an absolute prima facie case of suicide.
(shotgun fires)
- Fentanyl is a powerful
synthetic painkiller,
similar to morphine, but
100 times more potent.
And the autopsy also revealed the presence
of a diazepam like substance,
and this could possibly be Rohypnol.
- The smoking gun is the heroin level.
70 times the lethal dose
for the average person,
three times for the most severe junkie,
forensic pathological experts
say there's never been
one case documented in
the history of humankind,
with so much heroin in somebody's system.
- Kurt did have an exceptionally
high level of heroin
in his system when he died.
But I believe there's
an explanation for this,
and the other factors people
point to as proof of foul play.
After shotgun deaths, there
is a lot of blood loss,
and the medical examiner
may only be able to
get blood from the heart to sample.
As Kurt shot himself soon
after injecting the heroin,
it hadn't had a chance to
distribute throughout his body.
The veins drain directly into the heart,
so the drug is concentrated there,
giving a much higher reading than normal.
The lack of fingerprints
can also be explained.
The police report says that
they took four latent prints,
but they were of poor quality
and couldn't be identified.
Now keep in mind,
the gun had lain for three
days in a damp environment,
and this is not good for fingerprints,
and I believe this explains
why the police were unable
to find usable prints on that weapon.
Finally, the differences
in the handwriting
on the suicide note are notable.
But I think you can look at this,
and see that in the
latter part of the note,
Kurt wrote this while under
the influence of drugs,
and a police expert looked at this,
and confirmed that this indeed
was the handwriting of Kurt Cobain.
For these reasons,
I believe that Kurt Cobain
did indeed kill himself,
and I think I've
discovered the reason why.
- [Narrator] Smashing Pumpkins.
- D'arcy and Billy were shouting
at each other all the time.
- In a lot of ways I mean this is like,
the completion of everything,
what was started is over.
- [Narrator] Breaking the
Band, all new next, on Reelz.
(bright acoustic music)
- [Narrator] Discover new
San Pellegrino Essenza.
A twist of mediterranean flavors,
with the gentle bubbles of San Pellegrino.
Add a twist of flavor.
San Pellegrino Essenza,
tastefully Italian.
- Now that we're banking with Chime,
we get paid up to two days
early with direct deposit.
- Hey I just got paid.
Hi Boo, that's my girlfriend.
Just kidding it's Chime.
- [Narrator] Start banking
with Chime today, at chime.com.
- [Narrator] When you start with
a better hotdog from Oscar Meyer--
- That's no way to treat a dog.
- You can do no wrong.
- Where did you learn that?
- The internet.
- Yeah.
- Mm!
(upbeat percussive music)
- [Narrator] With no
artificial preservatives
or added nitrates or nitrites,
it's all for the love of hot dogs.
- Okay, it was an accident.
- He was tickling me and--
- Stop it!
- (laughs) Yeah, whoops!
But Julie has Resolve Pet Expert,
its latest formula attacks
odors at the source.
No odor, no stain, no nothing.
Whatever happens, no big deal, Resolve.
- It's about time they gave
left and right Twix their own packs.
They got about as much in common
as you a mortician and me an undertaker.
- Or you a janitor and me a custodian.
- Or you a ghost and me a spirit!
- [Narrator] Left and right
Twix packs, it's time to deside.
(upbeat music)
- Oof!
- Arm & Hammer plus Oxi Clean
with Odor Blasters detergent.
It eliminates tough odors
and blasts away the oof!
For a clean that will leave you in--
- Aah!
- At a fraction of the cost,
in packs and liquid.
Arm & Hammer, more power to you.
- [Narrator] Saddle up,
the Rodeo King is now part
of the King's Collection.
Two flame-grilled patties,
melted American cheese,
stacked with bacon, onion
rings and barbecue sauce.
Crafted by hand, grilled by flame.
It's the Rodeo King, only at Burger King.
(board applauding)
(funky music)
♪ Oh it's your thing ♪
♪ Do what you wanna do ♪
♪ I can't tell you ♪
♪ But I'm trying to ♪
♪ It's your thing ♪
(phone rings)
♪ Do what you wanna do ♪
♪ I can't tell you ♪
(funky music)
- [Narrator] Protect your
pet with the number one
name in flea and tick
protection, Frontline Plus.
Trusted by vets for nearly 20 years.
(fast-paced electronic music)
- [Narrator] Kurt Cobain died from
a single shotgun wound to the head,
in what police said was a suicide.
Many people have disputed this conclusion,
using the level of morphine
found in Kurt's body,
to argue it would have
been impossible for him
to have time to load a
gun and shoot himself.
(shotgun fires)
- I have shown how the length of time
that Kurt Cobain went undiscovered,
and the location where the
blood sample was taken,
could have had an effect
on the toxicology analysis.
So I am ruling out foul play as being
involved in some way with his death.
I believe that Kurt Cobain
did indeed kill himself,
and the evidence for this
rests in his family history.
(young Kurt drumming)
(ambient Music)
We know that Kurt was diagnosed
at age nine with ADHD,
attention deficit hyperactivity disorder.
What wasn't known is that he was also
likely suffering from bipolar disorder,
and that used to be known
as manic depression.
- Kurt's mother told me he
suffered from bipolar disorder,
and it made sense when you saw how
he was doing kind of wild, crazy things,
because that typifies bipolar disorder.
(light percussive music)
- It's a mood disorder
that's punctuated by
this very polarized way of behaving.
This kind of addicted
workaholic that you know,
wouldn't stop wanting to
get things to perfection,
that you know, wanted to
find the best drummers,
wanted to find the best riffs,
wanted to make the most amazing music.
And then this other side,
which was a depressive,
that just felt never quite good enough.
(moody music)
It's a very difficult
condition to live with,
and one that needs both proper medication,
and proper psychological support.
- I've not been able to find any evidence
that Kurt Cobain was ever
treated for bipolar disorder,
but I have discovered that
depression and suicide
ran in the Cobain family.
(brooding electronic music)
- I have lost two uncles and then Kurt.
They were the same age when
they killed themselves,
because I remember Uncle Leland saying,
"Oh my gosh, you know in a
few years I'll be that age."
And he was worried that he
would kill himself then.
- I've also discovered that
the chronic stomach pain
that Kurt thought he had been cured of,
had returned in the
weeks prior to his death.
(light symphonic music)
- I think the reason
that Kurt killed himself
can be summed up in one word, pain.
He was in such pain, both emotional,
psychological and physical,
that he just could not stand it anymore.
He'd rather be dead than alive.
- It's one of those terrible
ironies of his life,
that he worked so hard
to become something,
and then once he did, he
didn't like it very much.
- I sincerely believe that
Kurt committed suicide,
he clearly was not happy, running away,
hiding, upping his usage,
not trusting anyone.
- Kurt did appear happy in
the months before he died.
- [Kurt's Voice] Ever
since I've been married
and I've had a child, I've
never been more optimistic.
- [Dr. Hunter] But I
think this was a facade.
- When you see that kind
of happiness in somebody
that you know has been
suicidal, watch out,
because that usually means that they have
made the decision to kill themselves,
and now they're feeling relief.
- Having considered all
of the medical evidence,
I believe suicide is the best explanation
for Kurt Cobain's death,
and this I think is how it happened.
(skies thundering)
(slow piano music)
- [Narrator] April 5th, 1994, 6:00am,
the day of Kurt Cobain's death.
Kurt removes the 20-gauge shotgun
from its hiding place in his closet,
and heads to the room above his garage.
Once there, he finishes his suicide note,
which he leaves in a planting tray,
and spears with the red
ballpoint pen it's written in.
He unzips the bag holding his shotgun,
he takes three cartridges out
of a box, and loads the gun.
He smokes five cigarettes
as he sits on the floor,
before preparing his final hit of heroin.
It contains so much of the
drug that once injected,
it would kill him within a minute.
(fast-paced nervy music)
After injecting the heroin,
Kurt places the gun barrel in his mouth,
and pulls the trigger.
(shotgun fires)
He dies instantly.
- I believe that Kurt
Cobain killed himself,
whilst suffering from
the untreated effects
of his mental illness, bipolar disorder.
His depressed mental state
was further exacerbated
by the physical pain of
his stomach condition,
and the decline in his
mental and physical state,
from his excessive use of heroin.
(stirring symphonic music)
- [Narrator] Kurt's death
left a generation in mourning,
but his image untarnished by age and time.
- He'd be turning 50,
and you can speculate on
what it was he'd be doing,
had he lived, but doing the
nostalgia tour with Nirvana,
slightly fatter and balder
playing all their old hits,
I don't think he would have gone for that.