(soft rock music)
- [Announcer] Then, she
ruled the UK for decades.
Don't miss a new season of Victoria,
British television at its best.
(intense orchestral music)
(intense electronic music)
- [Announcer] This is
BBC World News America.
(intense electronic music)
Funding of this presentation
is made possible
by the Freeman Foundation,
and Kovler Foundation, pursuing solutions
for America's neglected needs.
(intense electronic music)
- Wow.
- That is unbelievable.
♪ Trying so hard not to let it show ♪
- I'm flying.
♪ Swear I can touch the sky ♪
- [Protesters] No more war.
♪ I'm 10 feet tall ♪
- Stay curious.
- Yes.
- [Announcer] And now, BBC World News.
(intense electronic music)
- This is BBC World News America.
Reporting from Washington,
I'm Laura Trevelyan.
Count down to the State
of the Union Address.
President Trump will call for unity
in front of a deeply divided Congress.
- [Nick] Mr. Neeson, are
you sorry for what you said?
- [Laura] Actor Liam
Neeson says he's no racist
after his desire for
revenge causes an uproar.
- Racist.
- Photograph was the very first picture
I ever took in war.
- Plus Sir Don McCullin's camera captured
the human cost of battle.
We'll hear how he turned his
lens on the home front too.
Welcome to our viewers
on public television
here in the US and around the globe.
Washington is poised
for tonight's State of the Union
Address by President Trump.
Aides say he'll call for
bipartisan cooperation and unity.
Mr. Trump will deliver
his primetime address
to a divided Congress,
one that's still smarting
after a 35-day partial government shutdown
over the president's call for
a border wall with Mexico.
For more on what we can expect tonight,
the BBC's Katty Kay joined me earlier.
White House aides say
that this address is going
to be all about committee,
but given just how
divided the two sides are,
can anything really be
achieved, do you think?
- Look, I think what the
president wants to do tonight is
to reach out to voters in the middle
with some sense of unity
and bipartisanship.
We'll hear that tone.
It's being written into
his speech at the moment,
and then also appeal to his base
with a tougher line on
immigration and that border wall.
President Trump knows
that he's not going to get
a television audience this big again
until the 2020 reelection
campaign is well under way,
so he's got that political
timetable in mind.
Juggling those two things
is going to be tricky
in terms of tone, and we all know,
Laura, that what is
said in a speech tonight
on Capitol Hill can very
quickly be overturned
with just one Tweet tomorrow morning.
- It can indeed.
Katty, is this really laying out
the battle lines for the 2020 election?
- Yeah, I think it is.
There are areas where the president,
and the Republicans, and
the Democrats do agree.
They could do a big
deal on infrastructure,
and I suspect we'll hear
the president reach out
to Democrats on an issue like that.
The trouble is, there is so little trust
on the Democratic side of this president
that, are they willing
to give him some kind
of a deal that he can
then take home and say,
you see, look, I've managed
to achieve something?
The 2020 reelection campaign, in a sense,
is starting right now.
We've already had those
Democratic candidates
who have launched their bids.
They're going to be sitting
right in front of the president.
Tonight is his big audience, also,
to talk about what he's achieved,
and what he can still achieve,
and of course, the spectacle
of all of this crowned
by Nancy Pelosi, Laura,
sitting right behind him,
the Democrat who has just given him
a very tough time, a
tough run for his money,
over that government shutdown.
You're right, the 2020
reelection campaign is all over
this State of the Union Address.
- Katty, what will you be watching for
when you see Nancy Pelosi there,
the symbol of divided government,
watching over the president?
- Yeah, I mean, it's almost
a kind of visual reminder
in every shot because, in
these States of the Unions,
you have the president, and then you have
the two people, Mike
Pence and Nancy Pelosi,
sitting behind him, and
they're in almost every shot.
It's almost a visual reminder for people
of this new tougher political landscape
that President Trump now faces.
I'd be surprised if
she gives him much more
than a cursory round of
applause at the beginning.
The rest of the time, expect her
to sit pretty stone-faced
while Vice President Mike
Pence sits there cheering.
That's the kind of prospect
that always comes up
in States of the Unions.
Remember, it's not just Nancy
Pelosi sitting behind him.
It's all those newly-elected members
of the Democratic House
of Representatives sitting
in front of him.
This is a very different
State of the Union audience
in that chamber than it
was for him a year ago.
- Katty Kay, thank you.
Well, the State of the Union
Address is a marquee event,
a speech which is
rewritten multiple times.
The White House says the
president has been going
through tonight's pages with his Sharpie,
reworking the material.
It's all about striking the right tone
while leaving an impression for the ages.
Here are some examples from the past.
- Don't let anyone tell you
that America's best days are behind her,
that the American spirit
has been vanquished.
- The era of big government is over.
(audience claps)
- Terrorist allies constitute
an axis of evil arming
to threaten the peace of the world.
- Well, for more on the significance
of these major addresses and the work
that goes into them, I spoke
earlier with Stephen Krupin,
a former speechwriter for President Obama.
State of the Union Address is
a highly choreographed one.
Just how high are the expectations
of this speech tonight?
- The White House would like
to set out an expectation
that this is going to be,
as you and Katty mentioned,
a speech about unity, which I think
is just about as credible
as much else coming out
of the Trump White House.
The State of the Union Address happens
in the House chamber.
It doesn't happen in a vacuum,
and we can't listen to
what he says tonight
without regard for what he said yesterday
and what he'll say tomorrow.
If the president continues
to stigmatize immigrants,
continues to spurn
allies, how is that unity?
If the White House has
to go to such extremes
to make that case that this
is a speech about unity,
if he does that one day a year
using sentences that we
know don't sound the way
that President Trump,
as we all know, sounds,
it kind of gives lie to the whole charade.
- But as a former speechwriter,
just how much work would
go into a speech like this?
- An enormous amount of work.
It starts months before the speech itself.
It is a speech
where not only the White
House is focused on it,
the communications, the
policy, the research parts
of the White House, but also
all the cabinet agencies.
Everyone wants their line
in that precious real estate
because, when the president
of the United States says it
to the country and the world,
it elevates their issue.
- [Laura] Also, typically,
these speeches have a big,
historical sweep, don't they?
Because the tradition began
with George Washington himself.
- [Stephen] It is, it is historical,
and the history of it is
all about accountability.
It is not the president
speaking to the country
and the world from the Oval Office.
It is the president coming
to the people's house
at the invitation of the people's house,
which underscores that our
democracy is about checks
and balances, and that the president,
whether he likes it or not,
needs the Congress to pass his agenda.
- Although we hear from the president,
especially this one, in a variety of ways,
on Twitter, we have
impromptu press conferences,
but as an occasion, do you feel
that the State of the
Union retains its power?
- I think it retains its
power in a general sense
because it is the president speaking
to all of the government assembled,
as well as the American
people beyond and the world,
who are listening to what he has to say.
In this particular case,
I think it does him a disservice.
I think the State of the
Union Address is perhaps
President Trump's most unnatural venue.
It is, at its best, an
opportunity to call for unity,
which President Trump does not do,
he speaks to his base, he is divisive,
is an opportunity to speak the truth,
which we know President Trump doesn't do.
It's an opportunity for
careful rhetoric, and we know
that President Trump is careless
at best with his rhetoric.
- We'll see how he does tonight,
but President Ronald Reagan
started this tradition
of mentioning in his speech people
that he had brought as guests.
That's really become quite a
bit of stagecraft, hasn't it?
- It's absolutely stagecraft.
It's an important way to show
that the policy that is spoken about
in the State of the Union
Address actually affects
real people, real Americans,
that it's not just
abstract political theory.
What President Obama
tried to do, for example,
was talk about people who
represented the struggles,
or the challenges, or the aspirations
that the American people
were going through.
In 2015, there was a family
named the Erlers from Minnesota
whose story of perseverance
was a nice metaphor
for the way the country was coming out
of the Great Recession.
What was different
about the way President
Obama used these guests is,
it spoke to the country's hopes.
President Trump, as we'll see tonight,
just like last year, often uses guests
in an exploitative way to
speak to our basest fears.
- [Laura] Stephen Krupin,
we'll see what the speech has
in store for us tonight.
Thank you for joining us.
- Thank you, good to be here.
- Now, the actor Liam
Neeson says he's no racist
after admitting he once
walked the streets looking
for a black man to kill.
The Hollywood star describes a primal urge
for revenge after a friend was raped
by someone she said was black.
Neeson insists that race had
nothing to do with his actions.
The BBC's Nick Bryant
has more from New York.
- [Nick] After his explosive comments
about rape, revenge, and race--
Mr. Neeson, are you
sorry for what you said?
Liam Neeson arrived at this
Manhattan television studio
not to make an apology,
but to offer an explanation.
- I'm not racist.
- [Nick] He admitted to setting out
to kill an innocent black
man nearly 40 years ago
after someone close to
him was allegedly raped
by a black man.
- Would you have had the same reaction
if your friend had said
it was a white man?
Would you have wanted
to go out and kill him?
- If she'd have said an Irish, or a Scot,
or a Brit, or a Lithuanian,
I know I would've had the same effect.
I was trying to show honor to,
stand up for my dear friend
in this terrible medieval fashion.
I'm a fairly intelligent guy,
and that's why it kinda shocked me
when I came down to earth
after having these horrible feelings.
Luckily, no violence occurred
ever, thanks be to God.
- What makes you think you can kill a man?
- I read it in a crime novel.
Carl's dead.
Tell me what happened.
- [Nick] Promoting his new movie,
the theme of which is murderous revenge,
the actor had given an interview,
telling how he sought retribution
after hearing about the rape.
There's been outrage at those remarks,
but some have commended his
honesty, and viewers saw
his own personal torment
written across his face.
- Wow, I'm just shocked.
I couldn't believe he would
say something like that.
I thought he was a good guy.
- It makes you have a little bit of fear,
but we have to push through that
and find the love.
- He was on a public platform.
- [Nick] At this black
theater company in London,
young actors gave us their reaction.
- Him using that language in the interview
in light of his influence is naive.
- I agree with you, I don't
think we should vilify him,
but the statement that
he made is problematic.
- For Liam Neeson,
today was supposed to be
about promoting his new movie,
but instead, he's trying
to salvage his reputation.
(reporters shout)
The 66-year-old has been one
of Hollywood's more bankable stars.
Will he face a backlash at the box office?
Nick Bryant, BBC News, New York.
- In other news now, high level talks
between Afghan officials
and the Taliban are
taking place in Russia.
This comes off the back of the US
and the Taliban announcing
they made progress in
peace talks last month.
Afghan government officials
who are not taking part
in the talks criticize the
meeting as counterproductive.
Former Manchester United manager
Jose Mourinho has been sentenced
to a year in prison in
Spain for tax fraud,
but will not serve any time behind bars.
He accepted the sentence as part
of a deal with prosecutors
in a wider investigation
into alleged tax evasion
by some of Spain's top footballers.
Instead, he'll pay a fine
of 1.75 million pounds.
Pope Francis, who's just returned
from a tour of the Middle East, has,
for the first time, publicly admitted
that clerics have sexually abused nuns.
Speaking during a midair news conference,
he said the church was aware
that priests and bishops had abused nuns,
and was working on the issue.
Pope Francis added that his predecessor,
Pope Benedict, was forced to shut down
an entire congregation of nuns
who were being abused by priests.
Police in Paris say the fire
that engulfed a residential
building during the night,
killing 10 people, was
possibly started on purpose.
They've arrested a woman who lived there.
At least 30 other people have
been injured in the blaze.
Lucy Williamson reports now from Paris.
- [Lucy] The fire brigade
described it as apocalyptic,
an eight-story apartment
block hollowed out by flames,
its living rooms, bedrooms,
hallways fuel for the inferno.
Tiny ladders hung from windows,
a lifeline, allowing
firefighters to get in.
It was a scene of chaos,
their captain said,
the search for residents
through the smoke-filled
floors accompanied
by the sound of screaming,
many survivors found clinging
to windowsills or roofs.
- The alarm went off after midnight.
It was already black with smoke.
I live on the top floor.
I had to climb across
several balconies to get out.
We hid in a corner with several people
to escape the flames.
- By dawn, the fire was under control,
but the search for victims continued.
When firemen arrived here in
the early hours this morning,
they found a building
hidden behind a courtyard.
With no way of accessing
it from the street,
their normal ladders were useless.
They had to use specialist equipment
to rescue people from
windows and nearby roofs.
Police are treating it as arson,
and are questioning a resident.
- A woman who lives in the
building has been questioned.
She is 40 years old and
has a previous history
of psychiatric disorders.
- [Lucy] Firefighters are working
to stabilize the building and
find the source of the blaze,
this sedate corner of
Paris now a crime scene,
a barren shell burnt bare of family life.
Lucy Williamson, BBC News, Paris.
- So many questions after that
devastating fire in Paris.
You're watching BBC World New America.
Still to come on tonight's program,
in Brazil, tales of survival
and devastating loss
following a major dam collapse.
The search for the missing continues.
(intense electronic music)
The UK music chain HMV,
which collapsed in December,
has been saved by a
Canadian record company.
Sunrise Records says
HMV has a bright future,
but it will close the flagship
store in central London.
The new owners say they'll be listening
to what their customers want,
including a greater
selection of vinyl records.
Here's Lee Zomazimba.
- [Narrator] Lunchtime, a quick stampede
to the record shops.
- [Lee] For decades, HMV stores have been
a huge part of life for music fans,
and for some of music's biggest artists.
- [Woman] Hello, Davy.
♪ We will remember ♪
(crowd cheers)
- [Lee] Now, while 100
stores have been saved,
27 are being shut down,
including the one where it all started
almost 100 years ago on
London's Oxford Street,
a perhaps inevitable consequence
of a music-loving public
who still enjoy shopping
in person, but who also
embrace consuming music online.
- People are ordering
online, they're streaming,
and really, there's
still a crowd of people
who want to come and browse.
- We rely on so many other things now,
streaming music, we stream
TV, we stream films,
and they've gotta find a business model
so they can survive.
- We get amazing support.
- [Lee] Enter Doug Putman,
owner of Canadian
retailer Sunrise Records,
HMV's new owners.
- We took over 80-some
odd stores in Canada
almost two and a half years ago,
and they're doing strong,
doing well, profitable.
We see HMV continuing on
in the UK for a long time.
- The challenges are significant.
HMV once made its money from huge sales
of CDs and games, all of
which have been plummeting
year on year, but even though many stores,
including, perhaps, this one,
their flagship, are closing,
they are still confident
that HMV can exist
up and down the country
through to its centenary
in 2021 and beyond.
Lee Zomazimba, BBC News.
(intense electronic music)
- In Brazil, the search continues
for those still missing after the collapse
of a major dam.
The death toll stands at 134,
with nearly 200 others unaccounted for
after an avalanche of
liquid mining waste swept
through the countryside.
Our South America correspondent
Katy Watson has been
to the site of the disaster
to speak to a woman who lost
six members of her family
and to a survivor who had
the narrowest of escapes.
- When the dam broke,
there was little hope
for those in the path of
the deluge that followed.
Panic as drivers struggle
to save themselves.
(Elias speaks in foreign language)
Elias was driving one
of the trucks that day.
"It sounded like an
explosion," he tells me,
but he soon realized what had happened.
- We saw the mud coming,
and I told my friend Sebastian,
run, the dam has burst.
You can see it on video, my truck moving
from one side to the other.
There was no way out.
We asked God to protect us.
Death was staring us in the face.
- They survived.
This was the aftermath.
His pickup, says Elias,
was like a grain of sand
tossed about in the chaos.
I meet Vanderlei searching
for the bodies of his brother
and cousin in the sludge.
This is their overturned truck.
- My world's ended.
I know I wouldn't find them alive here,
but if we are not on top of the search,
the authorities will stop looking.
- But in this sludge, the
recovery effort is slow.
There's been lots of rain
here in the past 24 hours,
and these firefighters
are returning to areas,
hoping that, with the extra water,
it might've displaced the mud,
and they can recover more bodies.
(helicopter whirs)
Every so often, they find something.
A body bag is flown back
to waiting families.
(Helena sobs)
The events of this past
week are still hard
to process for Helena.
She was to become a grandmother.
When the dam collapsed, that dream ended.
Her daughter, son, and pregnant
daughter-in-law were killed
when a wall of sludge slammed
into the hotel they were staying in.
Her ex-husband and his
wife died with them.
- [Helena] Camilla, Luis.
- Helena spells out the initials
of Camilla, Luis, his partner Fernanda,
and unborn baby Lorenzo.
- They were thrown I don't know where.
They died from cranial
trauma and asphyxia.
That was the coroner's verdict.
I don't even know if it was a slow
or a quick death.
- [Katy] The family's mourning
is made all the harder
because they haven't
found all the bodies yet.
In the distance, the search goes on.
Katy Watson, BBC News in Brumadinho.
- So much loss and grief there in Brazil.
Now, Sir Don McCullin has
trained his camera lens
on the horrors of war around the world.
His images from Vietnam won him awards
and respect in equal measure,
and even though he's now in his 80s,
the photographer has been
to Syria and to Yemen.
He's also photographed
inequality in his native Britain.
Now his classic images
are on display in London.
The BBC's Tim Muffett went to meet him.
- [Tim] Life and death
as captured by Don McCullin.
- Everything about me has
been very instinctive,
this knowing that I should be
in this place and that place.
- This exhibition brings together more
than 250 photographs by one
of the world's greatest photographers.
- This photograph is, you could say,
the beginning of my whole
life's work, really.
I started photographing the local boys
who I used to hang out with.
None of us were going anywhere in life.
This photograph was the very first picture
I ever took in war.
- This was the Cypriot Civil War, 1964.
- With the raincoat and the hat,
it looks like a still
from some mafioso film.
- [Tim] Were you scared?
- No, I was too excited to be scared.
I was scared of not getting pictures.
- [Tim] His reputation growing rapidly,
Don McCullin's assignments took him
to war zones across the world.
- That's the camera that
got the bullet on this.
Right, see it?
- [Tim] My goodness.
- [Don] That was in Cambodia.
- What makes a great photograph,
as far as you're concerned?
- [Don] First of all, it has impact.
I do not want you to walk past my pictures
without getting some message from it.
- [Tim] As well as war zones far away,
Don McCullin's also focused
on conflict and
depravation closer to home.
These pictures are all black and white.
Why is that?
- [Don] Because I think
black and white has
a much stronger way of
voicing itself to you.
It's a silent voice,
but I want it to be a
shouting silent voice
so you don't miss it.
- Some photographers bemoan
the ubiquity of camera phones.
It's so easy to take a digital photograph.
What do you think?
- People are now realizing that they want
to record their lives.
In a way, it's kind of enhancing
the love of photography.
Went to Vietnam two or three times,
but it wasn't until 1968
did I come up against a real opportunity
to stay in a battle for nearly two weeks.
This picture here, I
call it my crucifixion.
I put my cameras down.
I said to one of the
soldiers, "Look after these."
I had him on my shoulders, and I ran away.
I was 31 years old,
and I was strong as a lion, you know.
I could do it.
- [Tim] This image captured
post-traumatic stress disorder
long before the condition
was officially acknowledged.
- He was shell shocked.
They had no time.
The Marines don't respect
people who don't fight,
so they were treating him
very shabbily, really.
What we call the 1,000-yard stare.
Everything I've done in this room
is not gonna change the world.
It's just an attempt to show people
that it's wrong, that's all.
- Don McCullin's images of war.
Before we go, we want to wish everyone
a healthy and prosperous year of the pig.
After all, it's Chinese New Year.
The country's state broadcaster put on
its annual extravaganza.
An estimated 700 million people tune in
to this event every single year.
The holiday is marked by fireworks,
and by dancing, and by the exchange
of red packets filled with money.
Hundreds of millions
of people hit the road
to visit loved ones,
making it the largest annual
migration in the world.
Happy year of the pig.
I'm Laura Trevelyan.
Thank you so much for watching
BBC World News America.
(upbeat rock music)
- [Announcer] With the BBC News app,
our vertical videos are designed
to work around your lifestyle
so you can swipe your way
through the news of the day,
and stay up to date with the
latest headlines you can trust.
Download now from selected app stores.
(intense electronic music)
- [Announcer] Funding of this presentation
is made possible by the Freeman Foundation
and Kovler Foundation, pursuing solutions
for America's neglected needs.
- [Man] A new chapter begins.
(people cheer)
- [Announcer] Now, you can access more
of your favorite PBS
shows than ever before.
- This is the future.
- [Announcer] With PBS
Passport, a member benefit
that lets you binge many
of the latest shows,
and catch up on your favorites.
- We really are living
in the modern world.
- [Announcer] Any time you want.
- Wow, how about that?
- [Announcer] Anywhere you are.
- There's literally nothing
like this in the world.
- [Announcer] Support your PBS station
and get Passport, your ticket
to the best of PBS.
- [Announcer] BBC World News was presented
by KCET Los Angeles.
(soft piano music)
(lively rock music)
- I've always wanted to
know where we came from.
- [Announcer] On Finding Your Roots,
talk show host Michael Strahan.
- Unreal.
- [Announcer] Actor S. Epatha Merkerson.
- I'm blown away.
- [Announcer] History.
- You're looking at the
names of your family.
- [Announcer] Severed by slavery.
- It's unfathomable.
- They have names.
- [Announcer] Ancestry restored.
- Holy.
- Isn't that amazing?
(Michael laughs)
- [Announcer] Finding Your Roots.
- [Announcer] Join us for a new season
tonight at 8:00 on TV 26.
- This is national security
we're talking about.
We're not talking about games.
- We're not doing a wall.
Does anybody have any doubt
that we're not doing a wall?
- They're incredible job numbers
beyond anybody's expectations.
- [Announcer] Live coverage
of the State of the Union
Address tonight at 9:00.
(intense orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Vast, frozen, barren,
this is no place to be a lone wolf.
Here, prey are fierce,
and five times your size,
but the biggest challenge
of all, your competition.
To succeed, you need family, a pack
where the bonds of love
and loyalty are strong,
because here, strength in numbers
is the only way to survive.
(wolf howls)
- [Announcer] Wednesday at 8:00 on TV 26.
(soft vibraphone music)
- Won't you be my neighbor?
It's an invitation to help somebody know
love is at the root of everything,
love or the lack of it.
Thank you for whatever you do
to bring joy and hope,
light and love to our world today.
♪ Won't you please ♪
♪ Please, won't you be my neighbor ♪
- [Announcer] Saturday at 8:00 on TV 26.
- [Announcer] Today's
programing is presented
by WETA members and the following,
Joanne and Bill Conway
through their Bedford Falls Foundation.
(intense orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Tonight, a new season
of Finding Your Roots at 8:00.
Then join The News Hour for live coverage
of President Trump's State
of the Union Address.
That's followed by Christiane Amanpour
tonight on TV 26,
and on our WETA UK channel,
Doctor Blake and Doc Martin.
Then, she ruled the UK for decades.
Don't miss a new season of Victoria,
British television at its best.
(intense horn music)
- [Announcer] This is
Nightly Business Report
with Bill Griffeth and Sue--