- [Woman] Pressure.
- I cried my first time.
- [Narrator] Get live TV
only 15 bucks your fist
month at slingtv.com.
(alarm beeping)
(muffled breathing)
(clanging)
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
- Uh yeah.
Sorry.
- You know how we're
stuck in a tiny apartment?
- Yeah cause our credit's bad.
- Well I heard credit karma
could show us ways to improve it for free.
- Could that help us get a house?
- Yes.
- Nice.
- I'll be in my office.
- Yeah I'll be in mine.
- [Narrator] Take the first
step to better credit,
download the free credit karma app now.
- [Narrator] These women love the scents
in this ground-breaking art exhibit.
- It smells amazing.
- Luxurious.
- [Narrator] But what are they smelling?
- [Woman At Exhibit] Wait it's Suave?
(laughing)
- [Woman With Glasses ] It's body wash.
- No it's not.
(laughing)
- [Woman At Exhibit] I
can't believe this is Suave.
- Can I take this home (laughing)?
- [Narrator] Suave Body Wash,
fragrances as beautiful
as Bath & Body Works.
- [Narrator] Dave & Busters
introduces all you can play for 8.
Unlimited video games for 8 bucks more.
Sunday through Thursday
when you buy the new Craveable Combos.
Unlimited video games for 8
bucks with our Craveable Combos.
Only at Dave & Busters, more fun.
- (child's voice) Let's
talk about Haribo Goldbears.
- (child's voice) The
red is more gooder to me
cause it tastes like berries.
- (child's voice) They're really squishy.
- (child's voice) And then
mine gonna flied into my mouth.
(laughing)
♪ Kids and grown-ups love it so ♪
♪ The happy world of Haribo ♪
(dramatic music)
- [Max] All right we're back.
- [Nev] So yesterday we did some research.
- We don't know what to make of this.
- We're a little befuddled.
Okay so here's where we started.
So the first thing we found,
we searched his number, bingo.
- Look what we got.
Number for five years,
comes back to a Matt
(beep)
- This never happens.
He's in Florida where he says he lives.
So this was kind of a--
- Good.
- Surprise.
And he also has a Twitter.
Then there's some pictures back from 2012
that look like they're of him.
This would have been the Matt that you
sort of started talking to.
(dramatic music)
- Then we looked up his URL.
- We actually got a bunch of hits.
The first one was this.
A PlentyOfFish account that's up,
I don't know how or
when it was last active.
For a guy who lives in Kissimmee.
- 21 years old.
- This is.
- Six foot two.
There's also this photo.
It could be him.
(sad music)
- I'm not sure if I should
even make a comment.
I'm not sure what to say.
- What's, are you upset?
I can't tell.
- Do you mind if I take a second?
- Sure.
Yeah.
Take as much time as you need.
(ominous music)
- [Nev] You all right?
- Mmmhmm.
- [Nev] What was uh?
- I just got really warm
and just overwhelmed.
- [Nev] But like, good
excited warm overwhelmed?
- Um yeah.
- [Nev] Well that's good.
- Like this turned out to
go better than I thought.
So I'm completely speechless.
I hope that it's him.
- [Nev] Take as much time as you need.
I mean.
- That's okay.
- [Nev] But yeah I mean it is exciting.
It's cool.
I mean the guy seems legit.
- [Max] Good?
- Mmhmm.
- [Max] Regroup?
- Yeah.
She's got like a little overwhelmed
because I think she figured
that this was gonna end
up being like a huge
embarrassing disaster.
Anyway.
Looks like this guy is in Florida.
He's the right age.
Just to be sure we went
through his Facebook posts
and we saw that there was one girl
who seemed to be like
a good friend of his.
So we reached out this girl Crystal.
Crystal does know him.
She confirmed everything that
we assumed we knew about him.
- She also said she thought
he had a girlfriend right now.
- As far as you know is he
currently dating someone?
- She wasn't sure.
But she did say she thought
he had a girlfriend right now.
But we talked to Nick, his brother.
Nick said that Matt is not
in a relationship right now.
- [Nev] I mean at this point
we don't know what to believe.
(sad music)
(sniffling)
♪ Who am I ♪
♪ Who am I to me ♪
♪ If all I see ♪
(sniffling)
♪ All see is you ♪
♪ What am I ♪
♪ What am I to do ♪
- Wait what's wrong?
♪ If you love me too ♪
(door banging)
(crying)
- You okay?
- If he's real why is he hiding?
♪ Or is it you ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ We go big we go bold ♪
♪ Go bold ♪
- Woohoo!
- [Narrator] Critics
everywhere are in love
with "Spider-Man Far From Home."
It's a "Giant sized mega-movie."
- You're a superhero.
- It's kind of obvious.
- [Narrator] Spider-Man is
"flying higher than ever."
- This has always been the plan.
- [Narrator] "Holland and
Zendaya are charming together."
- She knows I told her.
- He didn't tell me I figured it out.
- [Narrator] It's "the
best superhero movie
"of the year including 'Endgame.'"
- Who else did you tell?
- [Narrator] "Spider-Man Far From Home."
- That was great!
- Ah that was so cool, I was so nervous.
- [Narrator] Now playing.
Rated PG-13.
(gentle music)
(gulping)
(happy music)
- [Narrator] Red Bull gives you wings.
- I'm Blue and I'm an ironworker.
Work is really rewarding
and brutal on my skin.
But knowing how I earned all that dirt
is pretty empowering.
When I get home the
first thing I have to do
is use the Dove Beauty Bar
to get rid of all the junk.
It helps me retain my natural beauty
by making it soft and nourished and clean.
And then on the weekend I get to dress up.
As a woman ironworker I feel
like I could do anything.
I could conquer the world.
I feel both strong and
beautiful at the same time.
- [Narrator] Dove cleans
and cares beautifully.
- This is what coverage looks like.
- This is what coverage feels like.
- But you don't have insurance
coverage you let it lapse.
- Don't worry, we've got coverage for you.
- Oh you guys are talking
about car insurance.
- Go to The General and save some time!
- [Kids] I'm a big kid now!
♪ I'm a big kid now ♪
♪ Went from baby bottles ♪
♪ To drinkin' from sippy cups ♪
♪ Went from wearin' diapers ♪
♪ To rockin' these rad pull-ups ♪
♪ We're 50 million strong ♪
♪ So put on your pull-ups ♪
♪ And help us sing this song ♪
- [Narrator] New size
fits smaller trainers.
- [Narrator] Dave & Busters
introduces all you can play for 8.
Unlimited video games for 8 bucks more.
Sunday through Thursday when you buy
the new Craveable Combos.
Unlimited video games for 8 bucks
with our Craveable Combos.
Only at Dave & Busters.
More fun.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] The Schick
Hydro Silk TrimStyle.
The tool you've been waiting for.
The only waterproof bikini trimmer
and hydrating razor in one.
Schick Hydro Silk TrimStyle.
Free your skin.
♪ They say we're too grown for fun ♪
♪ We say playful's never done ♪
♪ Don't fight the feelin ♪
♪ Just let it flow ♪
♪ Stackin' the bracket ♪
♪ Don't let it go ♪
♪ I've got a secret ♪
♪ The world should know ♪
♪ Let's stay playful Oreo ♪
- [Narrator] When you carryout
large three-topping pizzas for 7.99
Dominoes carryout
insurance has you covered.
Cause stuff happens.
Stuff like this.
- Ah!
- [Narrator] Just bring it back
and we'll remake it for free.
(crying)
- [Nev] Here's what we know.
Matt is a good-looking, young guy
from Florida who did live in California.
The only concern we have now is
why haven't you video-chatted.
Why hasn't he sent you
Snapchats of his face?
If he is real what's he not telling you?
What're we missing?
- Just kinda wanna get
off the floor (laughs).
- [Max] Sure.
- So here was are.
We've got some questions
that we're trying to answer.
If you definitely wanna meet him
then we have to decide that right now
and figure out what that means
and how we wanna make that happen.
- I definitely wanna meet him
but I'm terrified of heights
and I'm terrified of planes
so unless there's a different
way to get there I can't.
- [Max] We can work with that.
- Why don't we see if he'll come here.
I'm gonna call this guy.
Okay.
Ooh I gotta show her this photo I forgot.
I forgot after we hung up with Crystal
she texted us a picture of them together.
Like a recent photo.
So that, there he is.
- [Max] What do you think of him?
- Um well he's not ugly.
- I think he's stunning to be honest.
Just very handsome.
- (laughs) Oh my god!
- All right I'm gonna go call him.
- How do you feel?
- Nervous.
(phone ringing)
- [Matt] Hello?
- Yo is this Matt?
- [Matt] Yes.
- Hey how you doing?
My name is Nev from that show "Catfish."
I actually spoke to your brother earlier.
We're out here in Sacramento with Kim
and we were wondering if you
wanted to meet up with her.
- [Matt] But why would she call the show?
- She didn't actually write in to us
her friend Joe wrote in
and was concerned that maybe you weren't
who you said you were.
I think after five years
it'd be great for both of you
just to meet up and see what happens
and kind of move forward.
- [Matt] But it's not that easy.
I just got a lot going on.
My brother got out of surgery.
I just started a new job.
You know there's a lot,
there's a lot of factors in life.
- Yeah I just don't get it.
Why isn't he sending pictures?
Why is he chickening out from meeting you?
Or lying about it?
Something is up.
- We could come to you but I
don't know if you know this
but Kim is sort of very afraid of flying.
If it was possible would you come to her?
- [Matt] I'll meet her.
I do wanna see her.
- Okay great this is good
we're making progress.
- [Matt] All right.
- I'll see you soon.
- [Matt] Okay.
- All right, later.
- [Matt] Bye.
(sighs)
- All right so I talked to him.
He does wanna meet you.
I think we're gonna try and
get him on a plane tonight
so that you can meet up wit
him first thing in the morning.
- Wow.
Are you gonna be okay tonight?
- Yeah.
- [Max] You're gonna meet him tomorrow.
- [Nev] Hopefully we'll
get you some answers.
- Okay.
- All right.
He's flying all the way out here
so just make sure you're
ready to talk to him.
- Thank you.
(dramatic music)
- She is a nervous nelly.
- I mean now I'm beginning to wonder
if it was him avoiding meeting her
- [Max] Right!
or if she's just avoiding him
and he probably picked up on that like.
- [Max] Yeah she could've been
the one that bailed every time.
(calm music)
(heavy breathing)
(baby crying)
(happy music)
- [Narrator] Every baby is
born with a unique microbiome.
A living layer that protects their skin.
Nourish it with the Baby Dove Range.
Made with prebiotic moisture
and 100% skin-natural nutrients
to support baby skin's natural health.
Discover Baby Dove prebiotic moisture.
- It's about time they gave
left and right Twix their own packs.
They got about as much in common
as you a mortician and me an undertaker.
(laughing)
- Or you a janitor and me a custodian.
- Or you a ghost and me a spirit.
(laughing)
- [Narrator] Left and right Twix packs,
it's time to decide.
- When plan A doesn't work out
I get Plan B One-Step.
- It helps prevent pregnancy
by delaying ovulation.
- And it won't hurt my chances
of getting pregnant in the future.
- You can get it right off the shelf.
- Over prepared?
Maybe.
- Confident?
Definitely.
- [All] I've got this.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] The Schick
Hydro Silk TrimStyle.
The tool you've been waiting for.
The only waterproof bikini trimmer
and hydrating razor in one.
Schick Hydro Silk TrimStyle.
Free your skin.
(growling)
- Max, no no no no.
Max.
- [Narrator] Dog's don't
know what's good for them
luckily you do.
Greenies Dental Treats.
- [Narrator] Attention cancer victims
who used the weed killer Roundup.
A federal jury unanimously found that
Monsanto's popular weed killer Roundup
was a "substantial
factor" in causing cancer.
You may be entitled to
substantial compensation.
If you or someone you love used Roundup
and were diagnosed with cancer
call the number on your screen now.
Don't wait there may be time
deadlines to file a claim.
Call 800-830-1829.
That's 800-830-1829.
- [Narrator] Meet Michelle.
Michelle was a smile hider
until she straightened her teeth
with Smile Direct Club.
Michelle is a full-time
mom and a full-time CEO.
And the thought of adult braces was worse
than having a smile she didn't love.
So she straightened her teeth discretely
by joining the Club.
The confidence wherever you go,
grinning for generations club.
It's a club with more than half a million
satisfied grinners and a network
of more than 200 licensed doctors.
So stop hiding your smile
and join the Club at
Smile SmileDirectClub.com
- [Narrator] Large
three-topping pizzas for 7.99?
Dominoes carryout
insurance has you covered.
Cause stuff happens.
Stuff like this.
- Ah!
- [Narrator] Just bring it back
and we'll remake it for free.
(upbeat music)
♪ We go big ♪
♪ We go bold ♪
♪ Go bold ♪
(water splashing)
- Ah.
- Mmmm.
- Would you care for another
(in foreign language) darling?
- Yes my love (laughs).
(in foreign language)
- [Narrator] Red Bull gives you wings.
♪ Take your time ♪
♪ Build a home ♪
♪ Build a place where we all can belong ♪
- [Narrator] Give Extra get Extra
with new extra refreshers gum.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Whether you
dry, curl or straighten
you can visibly repair
seven types of damage
with Tresemme's repair and
protect seven with biotin.
Tresemme puts in the
work so you can work it.
- [Woman] Ugh another delay.
But you keep bouncing
like I'm a bouncy castle.
Oh yeah, five stops, zero leaks,
we're crushing this commute.
(trumpeting)
- [Narrator] Huggies Little Movers,
our best fitting diaper
that fits like a hug.
Hug on.
(Skype ringing)
- Hi!
- [Nev] What's up?
- [Laura] Dinner time.
- Hey.
- My mom's over.
- [Nev] Hey guys!
- Hi daddy.
- Hi Cle Cle.
Look how good she is with the spoon.
- I know.
- [Nev] So cute.
- She's having quinoa
and vegetables and beans.
- [Nev] Wow I love it.
We got up here, we met this girl Kim.
She's been talkin to this guy Matt.
We did the investigation
and from everything we found
it looks like he's him,
that he's actually the
guy in the pictures.
- Great.
- Something's not adding up.
Maybe they're both sort of awkward
and that's why they haven't figured it out
and met up yet but it feels like we're
still not getting the full story.
- I hope it's a happy ending,
I always hope for happy endings.
- It would be nice to get one.
- [Laura] Yeah.
(baby crying)
- Oh no.
I think Cleo's done with her dinner.
- All right go finish dinner.
I love you and I'll talk to you tomorrow.
- Okay love you babe.
- Bye guys.
- Bye!
(phone ringing)
- [Kim] Hello?
- [Nev] Kim!
Matt is landing soon so
we're gonna head over to you
and we'll be ready to go.
- [Kim] All right guys I see
you guys when you get here.
- [Nev] Great.
- [Kim] All right bye guys.
- [Both] Bye.
(ominous music)
- [Max] Who's that?
- [Joe] Hey.
- [Both] Joe!
- How're you guys doing?
- [Nev] We were hoping we'd
get a chance to meet you.
- [Joe] Kim actually called me last night
and she was like kind of panicked.
And she just like let me know that
there were some things that
she didn't tell you guys.
- Do you know what it is?
- Um yeah but it's like
it needs to come from her
cause it's not really my place to say.
(dramatic music)
(door creaking)
- Hey.
- [Kim] Hey.
(ominous music)
- [Nev] Who's this?
- It's uh, our kid.
(booming)
- What?
- Yeah.
- [Max] Wait you guys have a kid?
I wasn't sure if Kim wanted to bring
her into the situation.
She didn't want to make
Norma known at any point.
- [Max] Norma?
- Yes this is Norma.
- Okay.
- [Max] Pieces of the
puzzle are coming together.
- [Nev] Hi!
- After we moved in she got pregnant
and then we just didn't work out.
She hasn't actually--
- He doesn't know that, Matt
doesn't know you have a kid.
- [Max] He doesn't know that.
- Okay.
- She did not let Matt know
because he told her some things
that like made her not
want to bring her up.
- [Nev] What?
Like he doesn't like kids or?
Doesn't wanna have kids?
- Yes exactly that.
- [Nev] Right.
- Doesn't like kids,
doesn't wanna have kids.
- Mmmhmm.
- What do you then think of this guy
who you know could be
a potential step father
to your kid who doesn't like kids and,
- [Nev] Lives in Florida.
- [Max] And doesn't send her pictures.
- You don't want her movin' to Florida.
- Oh no.
No no no no.
- [Max] Right.
But you know that that's what
they've been talking about right?
(air blowing)
- Just add that to the list.
This guy won't send you a picture,
doesn't like kids,
doesn't wanna have kids.
This is turning into more
and more of a bad idea Kim.
(sad music)
- Daddy's gotta get you baby.
(baby crying)
I'm just here to pick her up.
Y'all doing your thing.
- I love you.
- Give kisses.
(kissing)
Give knuckles to, give 'em knuckles.
- Hey, boo boo boo boo boo boo boo.
- [Joe] It was great to meet you guys.
- Yeah you too man.
- Later Joe.
- [Max] Oh wow okay.
You're in trouble Kim.
- [Nev] So Matt doesn't
obviously know you had a kid.
- When I was pregnant and talking to him
I didn't get big until the very end
and at one point I was
actually supposed to come out
to see him but I went
into labor so I bailed.
- Of course you bailed.
- [Nev] Cause he was here
when you were pregnant.
- Yeah.
- You know he doesn't care for kids.
Do you think he could be
a good father to Norma?
- I hope so.
I mean I've never met him so I don't know
exactly how he is in person.
- You really love this guy?
You really think Matt is
like a good fit for you?
- Um I believe so.
- All right so it's all out there.
Matt's plane should have landed.
Let's meet at Discovery Park.
We've got a date!
- I'm ready.
- Are you?
- I think so.
- Okay Mr. Matt.
- Guys how am I supposed
to tell him about my child?
- You just gotta do it.
- Let's let him tell you first.
- He's gotta few things to answer.
We wanna know why he never
sent a picture of himself.
- [Kim] Mhm.
Why he didn't make more of an effort
to see you when he was in Sacramento.
Right?
- [Kim] Mhm.
We wanna know how he
really feels about you.
- I mean if he's the person he says he is
why not just tell me who you are?
- [Max] Maybe he's not
the guy in the pictures.
- The whole thing to me
just doesn't make any sense.
All right Discovery Park here it is.
Right here.
What I expected.
(suspenseful music)
- [Max] All right fingers crossed.
- Oh.
- [Max] Uh oh yeah.
I see someone.
That could be him.
- I'm ready.
- It's time.
- [Nev] Face your fears.
Let's do this.
(suspenseful music)
Is this him?
- [Max] It's gotta be.
Who else would be here hiding
in the shade of a tree.
- Oh my goodness.
Oh (beep).
- [Narrator] Tonight
they're getting hooked.
- This is just wild.
- [Narrator] Are you?
- Let's (beep) go!
- [Narrator] "Are You the
One? Come One Come All."
New episode tonight at 9 on MTV.
- [Announcer] Tuesdays this summer
Aubrey's a double platinum selling artist.
- I'm the mother (beep)
Beyonce of this (beep).
- [Announcer] From Making
the Band in Danity Kane.
- If one person in a
relationship thinks it's over.
- [Announcer] But will her ex.
- It's over.
- [Announcer] Get in the way of her next.
- Thank you, goodnight.
- [Announcer] It's Tuesday beaches,
when "Ex on the Beach"
returns on a new night,
Tuesdays starting July 16 on MTV.
- Boring cold pizza in a box?
Hiyah!
How bout unlimited pizza on the buffet?
Starting at 5.99.
Cicis unlimited pizza
buffet, it's unbeatable,
it's unbelievable, it's unlimited.
(ripping)
(popping)
(roaring)
(happy music)
(laughing)
(splashing)
(popping)
(sizzling)
(laughing)
(cheering)
(popping)
- [Narrator] See this?
It powers Olia.
For hair color this
stunning and healthy looking
every time you color.
Powered by 60% oils,
Olia propels color deep into hair
and without ammonia.
It's in the oils
Olia, brilliant color,
visibly healthier hair.
By Garnier, naturally.
(whistle blowing)
- Not running.
Why am I not running?
Because the DQ Summer Blizzard Menu
is only here for a few more weeks,
with seven great flavors,
like New Sourpatch Kids and Brownie Dough.
(whistle blowing)
- Not running.
(whistling)
- [Narrator] DQ, happy tastes good.
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] Nutro.
Non-GMO ingredients,
no artificial flavors.
All the energy dogs need
and nothing they don't.
Nutro, feed clean.
(dramatic music)
- Not many guys get that opportunity.
♪ Jump if they want it ♪
♪ Wooohoo ♪
♪ They can come and get it ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
(happy music)
- Whew what the what?
Okay wipe, pretty please do your thing.
Nice.
Nailed it!
(baby cooing)
- [Narrator] Huggies Natural Care Wipes,
gentle like a hug, hug on.
- [Announcer] The hottest sneakers,
impossible to get,
until now.
Every pair,
every grail,
always available,
always authentic,
never sold out.
Millions know,
now you do too.
StockX, now you know.
Visit stockx.com today.
♪ Trojan Man. ♪
- Hey Trojan Man.
I've been hookin' up with this girl
and I'm kinda nervous to
ask if she's my girlfriend.
- It's okay to be adrift
in the sea of emotional vulnerability.
Just don't forget your life jacket.
Explore with confidence.
- [Narrator] Introducing a
boost to your workout water.
(mystical music)
Electrolytes meet vitamins B, C and E.
With no artificial sweeteners
this is the new Propel Vitamin Boost.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] The Schick
Hydro Silk TrimSytle,
the tool you've been waiting for.
The only waterproof bikini trimmer
and hydrating razor in one.
The Schick Hydro Silk TrimStyle.
Free your skin.
- [Nev] Is this him?
- Who else would be here
hiding in the shade of a tree?
- [Nev] You're Matt?
- Yep.
(booming)
- Oh my goodness.
- Oh (beep)
- Max.
- [Nev] What's up?
Nev.
Thanks for coming out.
(ominous music)
- So I do have a few questions.
Just out of curiosity,
you got a girlfriend?
- No.
- Why no pictures of you?
Why won't you send me any?
- I don't like being
in front of the camera.
- Okay but for five years
you've been talkin to this girl,
how do you not send her a little video?
Just so she knows it's you or something.
- You are who said you were,
you weren't lying about any of that.
So then what's the holdup?
- I'm a secretive person
for the most part.
- I think the bigger question
is do you care about her?
- I do.
- In what way?
- Like it would suck if
something happened to her.
Like that's how I would feel.
- That's one way to answer the question.
- I mean I care about you.
I mean I was there when your mom died.
You were there when my grandfather died.
I mean that's kind of
hard to like brush off.
- Do you guys mind if I take a second?
- No come back here.
- Yeah stay here.
- [Kim] Can't.
- Yeah you can do it.
- The hysterics are nice.
- [Max] Kim!
- [Matt] This is.
- [Max] Kim.
- [Matt] Interesting.
- It's him.
- I know it's.
- [Max] He's good looking.
- I know.
- He's skinny though.
I can fatten him up.
(laughs)
(sighing)
- [Max] That was quick.
Is it weird seeing her?
- It's awkward under these circumstances.
- Sure.
(laughing)
- But like have you been?
- Just let them be weird with each other.
Here it is, we made it happen,
now you guys let's see what happens.
(dramatic music)
- [Matt] Anything else you gotta ask?
- So do you still not like children?
- I mean it's iffy.
Why?
- Well I haven't really
been exactly honest.
I actually have an almost
two-year-old daughter.
- Huh?
- [Kim] I have a child.
- And you decided now to tell me?
- Yes.
I mean like I get that I was lying
but can you really blame me?
Like you told me to begin
with you don't like children.
Which leads me to my next question.
Would you like to be her godfather?
- Hold up.
I've never even met her.
I'm just now finding out about her.
A child.
Okay now my anxiety's through the roof.
- She didn't meet you when
you came to visit because?
- I bailed because I went into labor.
(dramatic music)
- Kim why don't you tell
Matt how you feel about him.
- Do I have to do it with all of you guys?
- [Matt] There's a bench
over there if you wanna sit.
- Yeah you guys go sit go talk.
(heavy breathing)
- Okay.
The past five years I can't say
I didn't fall in love with you
because I did.
I guess I just have huge feelings for you.
Can you like not just stare at me?
- I'm at a complete loss for words.
- Okay so like this is
really like pointless.
I'm walkin back that way.
- Okay.
(heavy breathing)
- Here come over here.
- I just wanna see the water.
- Can we just talk?
- Sure yeah.
- Let's take.
- Give us a minute.
- Get out here.
- Can I go for a run?
- Yeah do it.
- Thanks.
(heavy breathing)
- Don't fall in the river.
- Okay so do you want kind of
a romantic thing with Kim or not?
- That I can't really decide right now
because I'm still trying to process
everything that's going on.
I would have to sleep on the whole thing
and maybe get a clear head out of it.
- That's fine.
We can meet up tomorrow but
I think by the time you leave
she deserves some sort
of clear answer from you
on where you stand.
Kim.
I think maybe that's enough for today.
All right so we'll take
Kim back to the car.
- [Kim] Nice meeting you.
- Same.
♪ You ran me on you let me down. ♪
♪ Cast your spell and spell it out ♪
- From his like behavior do
you feel that he is into it?
- I got an uneasy feeling.
- Well you're both awkward.
(laughs)
- These things take a second.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
♪ Don't give it up ♪
♪ So easy, easy ♪
- [Man] We'd love some help with laundry,
spray and scrub anything with a stain.
Wash the really dirty clothes separately.
- [Narrator] New Tide Pods with upgraded
four in one technology that
makes you fool proof clean
in one step.
- Oh ya did the laundry.
- [Narrator] It's got to be Tide.
(upbeat music)
♪ We go big ♪
♪ We go bold ♪
(swiping)
- Three words, warm strawberry jam.
(dinging)
- Three more words, perfect as is.
(swiping)
- Frozen bites just like ice cream.
It's science.
(dramatic music)
(calm music)
(heavy breathing)
(baby crying)
- [Narrator] Every baby is
born with a unique microbiome.
A living layer that protects their skin.
Nourish it with the Baby Dove Range.
Made with prebiotic moisture
and 100% skin natural nutrients
to support baby skin's natural health.
Discover Baby Dove prebiotic moisture.
- [Announcer] Someone is
going to be the first.
Someone is going to make waves.
Someone is going to blow up the game.
Someone is going to reinvent a classic.
Someone is going to start from scratch.
Someone is going to break barriers.
Someone is going to do that thing
you really really wanna do.
It might as well be you.
(dramatic music)
♪ Trojan Man. ♪
- Sex is the sandwich
and you can put whatever you want on it
as long as you put this on it.
(slapping)
♪ Trojan Man. ♪
- [Trojan Man] Explore with confidence.
- [Narrator] See this?
It powers Olia.
For hair color this
stunning and healthy looking
every time you color.
Powered by 60% oils, Olia
propels color deep into hair.
And without ammonia.
It's in the oils.
Olia, brilliant color,
visibly healthier hair.
By Garnier naturally.
(dog growling)
- Max no no no no.
Max.
- [Narrator] Dog's don't
know what's good for them.
Luckily you do.
Greenies Dental Treats.
- Fact is every insurance
company hopes you drive safely
but Allstate actually
helps you drive safely
with Drive Wise.
It lets you know when you go too fast
and brake too hard
with feedback to help you drive safer,
giving you the power to
actually lower your cost.
Unfortunately it can't
do anything about that.
Now that you know the truth,
are you in good hands?
- Ugh another delay.
But you keep bouncing
like I'm a bouncy castle.
Oh yeah, five stops, zero leaks,
we're crushing this commute.
(celebration chiming)
- [Narrator] Huggies Little Movers
our best fitting diaper
that fits like a hug.
Hug on.
(monotonous music)
(gulping)
(happy music)
- [Narrator] Red Bull gives you wings.
(upbeat music)
- I guess that you could
be Cleo's godfather.
- Me?
- We don't have one yet.
- I would be honored.
- But that's not official.
(laughing)
I have to.
- You just tossed that out?
I could be the godfather.
Thanks man.
- I mean I don't know who
else I'd ask to do that.
Yesterday was a weird thing for everybody.
But we got through it.
Today's a new day.
I think you should spend
some time with Kim.
- [Matt] Yeah of course.
- [Nev] All right.
(calm music)
- Hey guys.
- What's up?
What's up Norma?
- This is Norma.
- Knuckles?
- Hey!
- Hey yeah!
- She gives knuckles.
- I got her something.
- Gotta give her some knuckles.
- [Max] Aw.
- [Nev] Nice.
- Whoa!
- Say thanks.
- [Nev] Aw!
(laughing)
She loves it!
- [Matt] Knuckles.
- [Max] Yep.
- Do you guys wanna go inside?
- Sure yeah.
- Let's do it.
- Her dad'll probably be
coming to get her soon.
- What do you think?
Pretty cute.
- Yeah.
- [Nev] But you don't spend
a ton of time with kids?
- Mm-mmm.
- You're very, obviously,
not ready to like
engage with a child.
- Right.
- [Nev] That's cool.
(laughs)
(text dinging)
- [Nev] Is that Joe?
- [Max] Go go Joe said.
- Yeah I gotta take her out.
- [Nev] There he is.
Hey.
- Give mama kisses.
- Kisses.
- [Nev] That hair, look at
that hair, both of you guys
have quite, quite the head of hair.
All right, later Joe.
- [Max] Bye Joe.
- [Nev] See ya Norma.
Wanna get out of the house so
it's not so quiet and awkward.
- [Kim] That would be nice.
- [Nev] There's a place
nearby that has a nice
like sort of outdoor space
where you guys could chill,
have some ice cream and
like hang on your own.
- [Kim] Sounds fine.
- [Nev] All right cool.
So do your thing, hang
out, take your time.
No kissing.
(laughing)
Or kissing's allowed sorry.
- So you calm now?
- A little bit.
- Where are we going from here?
- Stop staring at me.
- I'm just asking, where
are we going from here?
(gentle music)
- Good question, you speak first.
- To answer your question from earlier,
the one that I keep avoiding,
right now a relationship for
me is not the best place.
(sad music)
But I've got no problem helping you out
if you need help with Norma.
I mean I'm okay with
being Norma's godfather.
You know I do care about you
as friends.
I mean as long as I have you in my life
that's all that matters.
(techno music)
- [Max] So where're you
guys gonna leave it?
- [Matt] As friends.
- I guess this is goodbye for now.
- Yup.
- Good to meet you.
- Same.
- Thanks for coming up here.
- I guess till I see you next time.
- [Max] All right.
- Well that was weird.
(laughing)
But also heartwarming.
(Skype ringing)
- [Both] Hey!
- Hey.
- Give us a little update.
What's been going on with you?
Tell us everything.
- Just going to school,
working and being a mommy.
- You weren't going to school
when we met you were you?
- [Kim] No I started
taking online classes.
- That's great, what're
you studying for or toward?
- I'm going for a surgeon.
- Surgeon? Wow!