- It got infected, so they
had to remove the bone,
like the skull.
- Francesca?
- Yes.
(funky upbeat music)
- If I follow normal protocol on this,
you'll end up with no car.
- [Announcer] This is the
courtroom of Judge Frank Caprio,
where people and cases
are met with compassion,
a different kind of judge,
a courtroom like no other,
this is Caught in Providence.
- Who's Mr. Holder?
- This is Mr. Holder, Your Honor.
- And are you here with him?
- Yes, I'm his counselor
at the Riverwood program.
- Okay, who's gonna do the speaking?
- I am at Mr. Holder's request.
- [Frank] Alright, what do
you wanna tell me about this?
- Basically he received the
ticket on Sunday morning,
it started all his first park--
- Saturday.
- I'm sorry?
- Saturday morning, I'm sorry,
it's not at all his first ticket.
- He's had 31 tickets.
- Obviously I'm his counselor
for significant reasons,
at the same time it's something
that we're working on
engagingly with Mr. Holder
and truthfully speaking,
the tickets are becoming
further and further apart.
He happened to have been parked
across from Parenside Park
in front of the old
Bank of America building
on this particular morning,
he was attending a church service.
Sometimes he goes there also
to meet up with his daughter,
who's currently in a homeless situation.
So we are hoping that Your
Honor could find a reason
hopefully to waive this and
know that we're working actively
in terms of keeping this from happening.
- Is he homeless now?
- Currently speaking he
lives with his father
at an assisted living
residence in East providence,
but actually we have an
appointment next week
with the Gateway group to
hopefully line up housing,
affordable housing in North Providence.
- Tell me about the program,
I don't know what the program is about.
- We're a social services agency,
we're under the Horizon
Group, we have two locations,
one in Providence, one
in Warren, Rhode Island,
you know, in the East Bay area.
From there on out,
Mr. Holder's been a
longtime client of ours
and I've been working as his counselor
throughout the last nine months.
- What's the name of the program?
- Riverwood, one word.
- Are you familiar with that?
- [Ziggy] No, but I am
familiar with Horizon,
I have heard of that.
- It's basically human
services and social work,
primarily the role of
the Providence program
is to provide affordable housing
for low income individuals.
- Based on your representations,
I'm gonna dismiss it.
- Thank you.
- But I want Mr. Holder to know
that this doesn't give you
a license in the future
to say it's okay, I'll
bring my counselor down,
I can get away with it, okay,
I'm doing this based
on his representation.
Do you understand that?
You explain it to him, when he gets out,
'cause he's homeless, okay, alright.
- It's our intention to
avoid it, if at all possible,
thank you, Your Honor.
- Okay.
I'm just trying to see
if he gives me attitude.
- Despite what you may be thinking,
I believe this motorist
actually made two wise
choices in court today,
the first, having his
social worker speak for him.
Can you imagine what would have happened,
if he had opened his mouth?
I think he'd still be
enjoying the hospitality
of one of our local
correctional institutions.
The second is that he waited
until he passed Inspector Kerrigan,
before he disrespected the judge.
Trust me, that may have been
the wisest move of his life.
- [Frank] Anthony Michael Giacobi,
good morning, Mr. Giacobi.
- Morning, sir.
- What do your friends call
you, they call you Tony,
they call you AM, what do they call you?
- I can't say what they call me.
- I expected that kind of an answer.
Where are you from, Nevada?
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah?
What are you doing in Rhode Island?
- What am I doing?
I moved back here stupidly.
(court laughing)
- Are you calling me stupid?
- I was thinking about it, but I--
(court laughing)
- Listen, I'm gonna tell you something,
that's not nice.
Mr. Giacobi, you're charged
with going through a red light
on Allens Avenue and Terminal Street,
are we watching these today?
We should watch it.
- Yes,
we need to see it, judge.
- Alright,
here's what we're gonna do, Mr.
Giacobi, I'm gonna watch it.
Now there are two lines on Allens Avenue,
there are two stop lines,
if you are passed the first stop line,
when the light turns red, I'll dismiss it,
if you're not passed it,
it's gonna cost you 85 bucks,
we're gonna take a look
at it, look up here.
- [Ziggy] It's already red,
judge, show the time link,
it was red for 16.2 seconds, judge.
- If I look at this,
I look at this every day
and I'm supposed to know
that when the light clicks
three times, that it's red,
I'm supposed to know that,
I think we're all supposed to know that.
So they send me this kind of a video,
in a court of law, I can't
tell what color the light is,
I know it changed three
times, Inspector Quinn,
but it went from white to white to white.
- No, it didn't change at all, judge.
It stayed red according to the notice,
but according to the video,
I agree with you, judge,
I couldn't determine as to whether--
- No, I am not convinced by
clear and convincing evidence,
they didn't present clear and
convincing evidence to me,
that the light was red, I
never saw red on the screen,
I saw it all white.
I know it changed three
times, but I don't know
if when it changed three
times, what color it was.
That's a very long story,
but the result is that I'm
gonna dismiss the case,
because the city has failed to prove
by clear and convincing evidence
that you went through a red light.
Now is there anything you wanna say?
- Thank you.
- Oh.
(court laughing)
He's never told me what
your friends call you.
What do your friends call
you, they call you Tony,
they call you Anthony,
what do they call you?
(bleep)
(court laughing)
- His middle name.
- Thank you, sir.
- Well, I guess we had it coming,
the judge did ask him three times
what his friends called him,
based on his response,
we know he wasn't lying,
he really is an (bleep).
- [Frank] Josev Parentos.
- Good morning, Your Honor.
- You've a parking ticket
on Thayer Street, sir?
- Yes.
That day I wasn't driving the car,
I was just getting out the hospital,
'cause I had brain surgery
and my son literally
parked at the corner of CVS
and I got in the car and the lady said,
"You can't park there,
it's a fire hydrant,"
and I said, oh, alright, I understand,
I've had brain surgery, I had my helmet on
and then she says, "Yeah, sure,"
she didn't really believe me.
I got in the car and then we left
and then I got in the mail, the ticket,
she didn't even give us a ticket
on the way she was or anything.
- Alright, case is dismissed.
- I appreciate it, Your Honor, thank you.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
- How are you feeling?
- Good.
- I can't hear you, speak into the mic.
- Alright.
I had brain cancer surgery
and then it got infected,
so they had to remove the bone,
like the skull of my head.
- The skull?
- Yeah.
- So that's why you're wearing a helmet?
- It's why I'm wearing a helmet, yes.
- Yeah.
- So hopefully
in October I'm good.
- Okay, we're rooting for you, good luck.
- [Josev] I appreciate it, thank you.
- I got divorced from him
maybe about six or seven years ago,
- [Frank] Yeah.
- right before he went to
federal prison for 15 years.
- You're telling me all
these bad things about him,
but when he comes in,
you let him use the car?
- [Announcer] Brought
to you by Credit Karma.
Get your truly free credit
scores at Credit Karma today.
- Why are you checking your credit score?
- You don't wanna live with
Mom and Dad forever, do you?
(blender whirring)
- I'm making smoothies!
- How do I check my credit score?
- Credit Karma, don't worry, it's free.
- [Announcer] Check your free
scores now at Credit Karma.
(coughing)
- It's just a cough.
- Yeah, right
and the Earth is flat.
(screaming)
- [Announcer] Treat your cough seriously
with Robitussin CF Max,
nothing lasts longer
and treats more symptoms
for your cough, cold and flu.
Robitussin, because
it's never just a cough.
- We're doing karaoke later
and you're gonna sing.
- Jamie, this is your house?
- I know, it's not much, but it's home,
right kids?
- Kids?
- Papa, Papa!
- Oh!
- You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
- [Jamie] Oh, yeah.
- This one is tiny like a child.
- Yeah, she is.
(laughing)
Ah, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most,
a Home and Auto Bundle from Progressive.
- Oh, sweetie, please, play for us.
- Oh, no, I couldn't.
- Please.
- Okay.
(singing in Italian)
(funky upbeat music)
- Now this is a beautiful car,
how much do I have to put down?
- To you, three grand.
- Not if you call 800-Next Auto.
Book 'em, boys!
- Huh?
(melodramatic music)
- It's a crime to pay more than a dime.
- One dime down.
- At AutoGiants,
AutoGiants in Temple Hills,
Woodbridge and Manassas,
but you have to call
800-Next Auto right now.
- 800-Next Auto.
- But our credit stinks.
- It doesn't matter,
when you call 800-Next Auto,
you get credit amnesty.
- If you bring home 350 a week,
you get up to $30,000 in credit.
- 30 grand?
- Yes, sir,
with only one dime down,
but you have to call now, 800-Next Auto.
- Acres of warranty pre-owned
plus new Mitsubishis in Manassas.
Call now 800-Next Auto, 800-Next Auto!
- It's a crime to pay more than a dime.
- One dime down.
- Plus credit amnesty.
Bring home 350 a week, get
up to 30 grand in credit.
- They're standing by now.
- At AutoGiants three locations,
but you have to call to get this offer.
- 800-Next Auto.
- [Frank] Kathy Acosta.
Kathy, you have two red light violations.
- Yeah, it wasn't me driving.
- Who drives?
- It was my ex-husband,
he lives in Puerto Rico
and the first one that he
got, he said he paid it,
now I get a second one in the mail
and I'm furious.
- Are you divorced from this guy?
- Yes, I am.
- [Frank] When did you get divorced?
- Well,
well.
(court laughing)
- A year ago, two years
ago, six months ago, when?
- Oh, I got divorced from him
maybe about six or seven years ago.
- [Frank] Yeah.
- right before he went to
federal prison for 15 years,
just to explain what a good citizen he is.
- Well, the fact of the matter is
that the ticket was
just issued last month.
- Yeah, he just left last month.
- Oh, he's your ex-husband, but he keeps,
he's your ex-husband, but you
still let him use your car?
- Well, I try to be fair.
- You're telling me
all these bad things about him,
but when he comes in,
you let him use the car?
- True, true,
that's against me for being foolish.
- No, no, it's not against you,
I'm just trying to figure something out.
- It's because we have a child together.
She's grown now, but.
- Let's take a look at it.
There he goes right through
the light, he don't care.
Let's look at the other one.
(speaking too far from mic)
Yeah, that was a close one,
alright, lights please.
Kathy, I think you suffer
from having a big heart,
I think you're just too kind.
- Suffered for a long time.
- Yeah.
- I've paid my dues.
- Yeah, I'm gonna dismiss one of these,
because you're paying.
- Yeah,
but what I wanted to do was
to have him pay both of them,
but on his license in Puerto Rico.
- Kathy, when you receive these summons,
on the back of the summons,
if you had told us who
was driving the car,
then he would be held responsible,
you didn't do that and the
time for that has passed.
So it's too late to do that.
I would love to help you, if
I could do it, I would do it,
but it has no effect, if
you had done it originally,
then we would have notified
the authorities there
and he would have had a problem.
Okay.
- Lesson learned.
- Good luck to you.
(funky upbeat music)
Jennifer Cruz.
Jennifer, get close to the mic.
- Good morning, Your Honor.
- [Frank] What is your daughter's name?
- Marlenny.
- What is it?
- She's very well behaved.
- Thank you.
- How old are you, honey?
- I'm five years old.
- Five?
You wanna come up here?
- Do you wanna go up there?
- [Inspector Kerrigan] Come on.
- Okay, you have three tickets.
- Yes, I don't wish to contend,
I was just hoping that
you could, the late fees,
I was hoping that you could take those off
and I'd pay the tickets.
- Okay.
Do you have an excuse
for any of these tickets?
- I know that the one
on South Main Street,
I had put just one quarter in,
because I was just going to get my BCI
and there was 20 people in there waiting,
so they were backed up.
- I wanna show you something,
so don't leave yet, okay?
- Okay.
- Okay, hold that.
Okay, you're gonna help
me out with these, okay?
- Okay.
- Alright,
now I've got three choices
and these are the three choices,
I can charge your Mom
number one is $50, right,
and number two is $100
and number three is $150.
So should I charge her number one,
number two or number three?
- Number one, Lenny.
- Oh, no, no.
(court laughing)
You can't help her, I've
gotta change it around now.
Okay?
- Okay.
- So what do you think?
- Number one.
- Number one?
Is that because your Mom helped you out?
It is, huh?
(laughing)
I think she cheated a little
bit, what do you think?
- Yes.
- Oh, she thinks you cheated.
Okay, well, I asked you to help me,
so I'm gonna take your recommendation,
it's gonna be $50, okay?
- Okay.
- [Frank] Alright, thanks
for helping me out.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- Alright.
- Your fine was
$980.
- Yes.
- What do you wanna say?
- First I am terribly sorry.
- No, I don't wanna hear it.
(light upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Let's face it,
the world could use some more.
♪ I'll celebrate ya ♪
♪ Appreciate ya ♪
- [Mother] Oh, another delay,
but you keep bouncing
like I'm a bouncy castle.
Oh yeah, five stop, zero leaks,
we're crushing this commute.
(triumphant music)
- [Announcer] Huggies Little Movers,
our best-fitting diapers,
that fits like a hug.
Hugg On.
(light melodic music)
- Shorten your cold by
almost half with Cold-Eeze.