- Position for them.
- Okay, Kimberly Dozier,
thank you for the expertise.
Appreciate it.
- Thank you.
(upbeat music)
- All right, it is the top of the hour.
Good Monday morning everyone,
I'm Poppy Harlow in New York.
Jim Sciutto has a well-deserved day off.
The breaking news we begin with this hour,
federal prosecutors have just unsealed
an indictment against Jeffrey Epstein.
Inside it, the alarming details of how
the politically connected
billionaire allegedly ran
a sex-trafficking ring.
Epstein is accused of seeking out minors,
paying cash to girls as
young as 14 years old
to have sex with him, and then paying them
to recruit other girls for him to abuse.
Next hour, these charges
will be announced in public,
a press conference will be held
with prosecutors and the FBI.
And then later this morning,
Epstein will appear in court.
Still unknown, what this
case could reveal about
his political connections, and
they include a British royal,
a former president, and the current one.
Trump, who once called Epstein,
quote. (audio dropping)
We have team coverage this morning.
Our anchor and national
correspondent, Erica Hill,
is here with me in New York.
CNN crime and justice
reporter, Shimon Prokupecz,
is live outside of the courthouse.
And Shimon. (audio dropping)
Happening on Saturday.
It was planned for today.
(audio dropping)
- Pointed out. (audio dropping)
These accounts also escalated.
Also saying. (audio dropping)
In some of Julie Brown's
reporting we should point out
the girls who, the victims
who she spoke with,
the alleged victims, talking about how
they didn't know it going
to, maybe, go that way.
Or they maybe knew it wasn't right
but they just, again, they were young.
They didn't get it.
And it also points out
in the indictment that
they believe, prosecutors
believe, he did know their age
and what was going on
because some of these victims
who are in here were asked
specifically about their age
and they said they didn't lie.
- Let's talk about the
powerful people in politics
that were friends, are/were
friends of Jeffrey Epstein.
Including former president Bill Clinton,
who, I think, records show,
flew on his jet several times.
President Trump is
quoted with glowing words
about him back in 2002.
- He is, in fact, we have that from 2002,
he talked about him to New York Magazine
saying that he's a fun guy.
"I've known Jeff for 15
years," he said in 2002.
"Terrific guy.
"He's a lot of fun to be with.
"It's even said that he
likes beautiful women
"as much as I do, and many of
them are on the younger side.
"No doubt about it, Jeffrey
enjoys his social life."
Obviously, that's seen in a
far different light today.
But you're right, there
is a connection here.
You mentioned former
president Clinton flying
on his plane multiple times,
being on his private island.
President Trump reportedly
at least once on his plane.
The two reportedly dine together.
At one point Epstein was
actually a member at Mar-a-Lago
and had been to Mar-a-Lago,
but then was barred,
at one point, after,
according to court records,
which Julie Brown also wrote about.
He was accused of sexually assaulting
an underaged girl there.
- I would be remiss not
to bring up with you
the current Labor
Secretary, Alexander Acosta,
who is very tied to this.
Because he was a big part of securing
this sweet plea deal for
Epstein back in 2008.
That got him very little jail time.
Charged with prostitution,
not sex trafficking.
And, by the way, that none
of the victims knew about.
- No, they didn't, so a
couple of points there.
Number one, you're right.
So Alexander Acosta, at the time,
was the US Attorney for
the Southern District.
So, he had to oversee this deal.
He had to, basically, say,
okay with a team of attorneys.
At the time, he said well, you know,
they lack the evidence
to prove (audio dropping)
violated federal law.
There's been a lot of
push back on that since.
But he, essentially,
had to sign off on it.
Well, the DOJ is investigating
how the case was handled.
We should also point out that in February
a federal judge said
this deal broke the law
because, to your point,
victims didn't know about it.
The terms of this deal, which it's
been said multiple times are, basically,
dictated by Epstein's
attorneys, powerful attorneys.
They didn't know about it.
The deal was kept quiet,
kept apart from the victims,
until a judge had signed off for it.
You can't do that, that broke the law.
- Erica Hill, thank you, great reporting.
Obviously, you'll be on this all day
because he's going to be in
court later this morning.
Let's talk about legally where this goes.
CNN Legal Analyst Renato Mariotti is here,
former federal prosecutor.
You're such a good voice for this because
you have actually prosecuted
sex trafficking cases before.
One thing that Shimon said, outside
the courthouse moments ago, that struck me
is that what may be different this time,
than the plea deal in 2008,
if this goes to trial,
is that they have three cooperators.
And those are, apparently,
some of the employees
that arranged this travel
of these underage girls
to be with Epstein, et cetera.
How significant is that?
- Well, it's important.
Frankly, I think the case
is gonna rise and fall
for the Southern District of New York
on the testimony of those cooperators.
These cases are very
difficult to investigate
they're very difficult to prosecute.
Often, minors who are abused
have difficulty coming forward
and testifying.
They have difficulty,
essentially, going through
and doing what they would need to do
to be a witness in a case.
Really, here, the testimony
of the cooperators
has to be strong in order
for the Southern District
to make it's case in court.
What I think this indictment tell us
is the the Southern District believes
that they have testimony that
can back these charges up.
- When you look at the
deal that was struck
that raised so many questions,
that the victims didn't know about.
What do you think the
questions are going to be now?
Not only for Alexander Acosta,
the current Labor Secretary
who was a big part of this, but the judge
who signed off on it.
- I have to say, there are
very significant questions
about Mr. Acosta's actions there.
Really, there has to be something
very significant behind
the scenes that caused
that series of events.
There's clearly misconduct
by not informing victims.
It appears, at some point,
there was misrepresentations
that were made to the court.
Very serious misconduct by
Justice Department attorneys.
Victims need to know,
particularly in cases like this.
When I did investigate
human trafficking cases
and sexual abuse cases of minors,
those victims are counting
on you, as a prosecutor.
They have a right to have access to you,
they have a right to be heard.
They are counting on you to
prosecute and act fairly.
- And it is interesting that
the federal prosecutors working on this,
that are going to hold
this press conference
in a little under an hour, are from
the Southern District of New
York's Public Corruption Unit.
What does that tell you?
- It could be a coincidence, it could be
they just have time on their plates.
But it also could mean
that there is some tie
to this case, either from the
angle you just talked about
or another, there's an obstruction,
potential obstruction provision.
Perhaps there is a public
official that could,
that is at least tangentially
involved in this case
and could become part of it later on.
- Interesting, all really
important questions
to be answered.
Renata Mariotti, thank you so much.
Also this morning, as more images
and reports come out
of inhumane conditions
at these migrant
detention facilities along
the southern border, the president says
he now wants the media to go
inside and see for themselves.
With me now is our Kaitlan Collins
she joins us from the White House
and Natasha Chen in El Paso, Texas.
good morning to you both.
Kaitlan, the president says he wants this
but there is a big difference
between saying that
and then the facilities
actually letting in journalists
with cameras unannounced.
- Yeah, and so far they've
been pretty hesitant,
even not wanting lawmakers
to bring their phones
into those facilities.
Of course, there are children there.
So, whether or not that
invitation is actually going
to go forward is still an open question.
But so far, the president and his aides
have been downplaying the reports
about these conditions at the border.
Here's what the president said when he was
on his way back to the
White House, yesterday.
- I'm gonna start showing some
of these detention centers
to the press.
We're gonna have of the
press go in and see it
because they're crowded,
and we're the ones
who were complaining
about they're crowded.
- So, the president there going after,
not only some of those
Democratic lawmakers
who have been reporting what they saw
when they've toured these facilities.
But Poppy, we should note, it's not just
any one, singular report
detailing these conditions
that they say are widespread
at these facilities.
Conditions like overcrowding,
some standing-room-only areas.
People going without hot meals.
But not only just from Democrats
it's coming from a report from
the president's own government.
And a highly detailed
and very specific report
in The New York Times
that came out yesterday
and that people should read
if they haven't seen it yet.
- They absolutely should.
And Natasha, you're there and you spoke
to a Texas State Rep who
says Border Patrol agents
have been trying for some time
to bring light to the conditions in Clint.
Which is probably why a number of them
were willing to speak to The Times.
- Well, that's right Poppy.
We were talking to
Representative Mary E. Gonzales,
she represents the Clint
area where that facility is.
She says that local leaders
like herself in the community
did not even know that children,
unaccompanied children,
were being processed
through that facility,
until news reports came
out in the last month or so
about the conditions inside.
She said, some of these
Border Patrol agents
who live in this community,
who have known her
for a long time, they have
been telling her about
how demoralizing and depressing
it is to work right now
in those conditions, because of what they
are seeing day to day with the migrants.
They've also told her about
how hundreds of children
at one point, were being
processed through that facility
in a space that's really not
designed for that many kids.
And being held there for longer
than they should be there
with limited shower and
shower facilities to wash up,
limited microwaves to
heat food to feed them.
Here's what she had to say about
her conversations with these agents.
- A lot of the people I
talked to who worked there
were saying, we have
been telling higher-ups
there's a problem.
And basically, those
pleas have been ignored.
A lot of the people who I talked to
have been in the Border
Patrol for decades,
23 years 24 years, this is
something very new to them.
They were never charged with
being caretakers of children.
At the end of the day, we have to realize
that my community is struggling with
a administration-made problem.
- And Gonzales did say that
she got to visit inside
the Clint facility last week when there
were far fewer children.
Many of them have now been processed out.
We did also hear from the Sector Chief
of this El Paso region today, who said,
now in this region they have
only 26 children in custody.
He disputes the reports of the
inhumane conditions inside.
But he does acknowledge
it's very possible agents
have been complaining about conditions
and overcrowding in the past.
He says, they've all been complaining
that there are just too many children
and not enough resources
to process them through.
- Thank you so much for the
reporting, for talking to her.
Natasha Chen, we appreciate
and Caitlin Collins at the White House.
All right, still to come.
The Department of Justice
is taking a new strategy
as it pushes again to try to
get a citizenship question
on the upcoming census.
We'll talk about that.
Plus, new fighting words
within the Democratic Party.
House Speaker Nancy Pelosi takes
on Congresswoman Alexander Ocasio-Cortez.
And later, the US women are heading home
with another World Cup title and ready
to take on a bigger battle, equal pay.
(upbeat music)
(wind howling)
♪ I want it that way ♪
- I can't believe it.
- That Carl brought his karaoke machine?
♪ Nothin' but heartache ♪
- No, I can't believe how easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
my car insurance with GEICO.
♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ I never wanna hear you say ♪
- Go Kevin.
(wind howling)
♪ I want it that way ♪
- [Announcer] Believe it.
GEICO could save you 15%
or more on car insurance.
(T-Mobile chimes ringing)
- [Announcer] Have a discount
with another wireless carrier?
T-mobile will match it.
Need a few more reasons to switch?
One, do you like Netflix?
Sure you do that's why it's on us.
Two, unlimited data, use as
much as you want, when you want.
Three, no surprises on your bill
taxes and fees included.
So, if you have a discount,
bring it to T-Mobile.
We'll match it and give
you great benefits.
(T-Mobile chimes ringing)
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Summer's not
stopping or slowing down.
So take advantage of all
of summer's opportunities
with our limited time
offers while you still can.
Hurry into the Acura
Summer of Performance event
going on now.
Visit your local Acura
dealer to test-drive
the 2019 ILX, starting MSRP 25,900.
(baby crying)
- [Woman] Be right there, baby.
Oops.
(stumbling and crashing)
Sorry.
(baby crying)
(Pop Goes The Weasel chiming)
- [Announcer] Unlike ordinary diapers,
Pampers is the first and only diaper
that distributes wetness evenly
into three extra absorb channels.
They stay up to three times drier
so babies can sleep soundly, all night.
Wishing you love, sleep and play, Pampers.
- We tried two different
real estate agents
who both promised great results.
But after almost a year on the market
we still hadn't sold our house.
Then we found HomeLight which promised
to get us in touch with
the top agents in our area.
We went with the agent they
recommended and it worked.
HomeLight's agents sold our
house when the others couldn't.
- [Announcer] HomeLight
compares data on millions
of agents, so you know you're getting
the best agent for your needs.
- Oh yeah, we recommend HomeLight.
- [Announcer] Get started for
free today at HomeLight.com.
(upbeat music)
- In one week, a lot
will happen in your life.
Wrinkles just won't.
Neutrogena Rapid Wrinkle Repair's
derm-proven Retinol, works
so fast, it takes only one week
to reveal younger looking skin.
Making wrinkles look so last week.
Rapid Wrinkle Repair,
pair with new Retinol Oil
for two times the wrinkle fighting power.
Neutrogena.
- [Announcer] Warning, this
product contains nicotine.
Nicotine is an addictive chemical.
Innovation has changed the
world, moving us all forward.
Isn't it time smoking changed too?
At Vuse, we push the
possibilities of vapor
so that ever decision, every
detail, goes into creating
what smokers really want,
real draw, real taste,
real satisfaction.
Vuse Alto, the perfect puff is here.
- [Announcer] Rated M document for mature.
Forget everything you
know about mobile games.
(shots firing and crashing)
And get ready to raid.
(individual roaring)
Explore, collect and fight.
(club thumping)
Choose your champions.
Defeat Terrifying bosses.
Win glory in PVP battles.
RAID: Shadow Legends, play for free now.
(upbeat music)
- This is Caitlin.
- And this is her husband Josh.
- Hello.
- Josh is in the military
and he's deployed a lot.
- Must be had with a family.
- It is, but since we
installed Ring in our home
I feel much more at peace.
Plus, it saves us a ton of money.
- And I like that Ring
is keeping my family safe
while I'm away, so thank you guys.
- No, thank you for keeping us all safe.
- You got it.
- To learn more about Caitlin, Josh
and the complete home
protection of Ring Alarm,
go to Ring.com.
- [Announcer] "Apollo 13" was
a real turning point for me.
- Houston, we have a problem.
- I learned the power of a true story.
How an audience begin to lean in when
they know you're dealing with the truth.
- All right, new team, new argument.
After the Supreme Court ruled against
the Trump administration's attempt
to add a citizenship
question to the census.
This morning, the Justice Department says
a different team of lawyers
will now take up this battle.
For more on why, Jessica Schneider,
our Justice Correspondent, is here in DC.
So, this is even after the
Supreme Court ruled against
them in this.
The administration sees
it as that important
that they're putting a new
team of attorneys on this.
What does it mean and why does it matter?
- That's right Poppy.
So, this will be a new team that will now
have to push a completely
different set of arguments
to try to get this citizenship
question on the 2020 census.
And we've learned that
the political appointee
who led the initial team of lawyers did
in fact, think that it made sense to get
a new team of lawyers on board because
they are really doing an about-face here.
It's a flip-flop that seems to
have been forced by the president.
Because, remember, it
was less than a week ago
that this fight seemed to be over.
Lawyers from the DOJ's
Federal Programs branch,
told the challengers to
the citizenship question
that the census was going to print without
the controversial question.
And then, those lawyers told a judge
that the decision was final.
But then, of course, we
saw that flurry of Tweets
from the president and he
insisted that he would push
his administration to find
a way to add this question.
Now, DOJ lawyers admitted, just last week,
to a Maryland judge in
a hearing on Wednesday
that they were really blindsided by
the president's tweets, here.
Especially since the DOJ
has been insisting all along
that a July 1st deadline
to print this census
was the absolute drop-dead deadline.
And now, all indications are that the DOJ
is continuing to press forward to find
a rationale to add this question.
Poppy, it is possible, I mean,
the Supreme Court said,
when they made that ruling,
that if the Justice Department
and the Census Bureau went back
and provided some sort
of rationale, possibly,
this question could be added.
But really, it seems the administration
is running out of time here.
They've already gone past
their own July 1st deadline.
Now, they could continue
to push it forward
but who knows if they would
even have time to add it.
Poppy.
- You know, just your
point, not to mention,
you know, if they come up with
a completely new rationale
and reasoning, what will
mean for Wilbur Ross's,
the Commerce Secretary's testimony.
When he talked about the
rationale, et cetera.
I guess if they win on this,
what are they going to put?
Like an insert in the census for everyone?
I mean, actually, how would this play out?
- Right, so logistically, that's sort of
the big question here.
The census, we know from DOJ officials,
it has gone to print
without that question.
But could the administration somehow
add on a citizenship question, by maybe,
adding supplemental pages,
supplemental questionnaires?
You know, the president has floated
the idea, even of an executive order
to mandate that this question be added.
But all of these options, Poppy,
they're sure to face these
continued legal fights.
We're already seeing it on two fronts
in federal courts in New
York and Maryland here.
And of course, we're running out of time
because we're less than
six months away from 2020
and the census needs to get out.
Poppy.
- Okay, Jessica Schneider,
thank you so much.
Ahead for us, new
attacks on Nancy Pelosi's
leadership style.
Will the speaker win out
in this latest new school,
old school battle?
(dramatic orchestral music)
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Award winning interface.
Award winning design.
Award winning engine.
The Volvo XC90, the most awarded
luxury SUV of the century.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] PNC Bank has technology
to help make banking easier.
(man yelling)
Like PNC Easy Lock, so you can
easily lock your credit card
when its maximum limit differs
from its vertical limit.
And Clover Flex for when you
need to take credit cards
when no one carries cash.
Or requesting a call to
help get a new credit card,
one that hasn't followed
the family goldfish.
(toilet flushing)
PNC, make today the day.
- Sun care is self care.
I used to not love wearing an SPF
just because I felt like
it was so oily and greasy.
But with Olay Regenerist with SPF 25
it's so lightweight, I love it.
I'm busy Phillips and I'm
fearless to face anything.
- I switched to MiraLAX
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives forcefully
stimulate the nerves
in your colon.
MiraLAX works with the water in your body
to unblock your system naturally.
And it doesn't cause
bloating, cramping, gas
or sudden urgency.
MiraLAX, look for the pink cap.
- [Announcer] At Wayfair.com we think
that when the big stuff
ships free it's just better.
♪ Cover better, brunch better ♪
♪ Crunch better, rock better,
roll better, whoa better ♪
♪ Jean better, clean better ♪
(doorbell ringing)
♪ Yeah, better ♪
- Oh, Wayfair has free
shipping, game changer.
♪ Fast better, free better ♪
♪ Everything's better when it ships free ♪
- [Announcer] Get free
shipping on orders over $49.
Shop better at Wayfair.com
♪ Wayfair you've got just what I need ♪
- You're turning on to the street
When you barely clip a passing car.
Minor accident, no big deal, right.
Wrong, your insurance company
is gonna raise your rate
after the other car got a scratch so small
you could've fixed it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that pen
and use it to sign up with a
different insurance company.
- [Announcer] For drivers
with Accident Forgiveness,
Liberty Mutual won't raise their rates
because of their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty, Liberty, Liberty, Liberty ♪
- Welcome to the hall of allergies.
Today we take a stroll down memory lane
to see how these other OTC
medicines compare to XYZAL
the latest in 24 hour allergy relief.
You see, XYZAL lasts up to
six times longer than Bendryl.
Works faster than Claritin.
And on first dose, provides
the same relief as Zyrtec
at nearly half the size.
So, for the latest in powerful relief
it's just as effective at
hour 24 as at hour one.
Be wise all, take XYZAL.
- Sir, please don't touch the exhibit.
- We use Angie's List because we
can always find great, local pros.
- For any type of home project.
- I use Angie's List because it's free.
- Free to read reviews.
- Check their ratings.
- They can even match my
project to qualified pros.
- [Announcer] Go to angieslist.com today.
(orchestral thunder)
- [Male Announcer] The
2020 race is revving up.
Live from Detroit.
20 Candidates, two big nights.
The CNN Democratic Presidential Debates.
July 30th and 31st.
Only on CNN.
- Have you been told you can't
get high-speed internet where you live?
Well, you can with HughesNet Gen5.
Experience the power of
next-gen satellite internet
wherever you live.
HughesNet Gen5 is fast.
You'll get 25 megabits per second.
Plus, built-in WiFi and
there's no hard data limits.
So, wherever you live, now you can do more
of everything you love online.
Connect on social media.
Stay informed.
Watch the latest videos.
(crowd cheering)
And help your kids get ahead.
No wonder HughesNet is
America's number one choice
for satellite internet.
- [Announcer] Act now to save big
with our limited-time offer.
Get free standard installation
by calling right now.
- So, what are waiting for?
Get HughesNet Gen5.
- [Announcer] To order
call 1-800-743-9610.
Be sure to ask about our
home phone service too.
Call 1-800-743-9610, today.
(upbeat music)
(orchestral thunder)
- All right, this morning, Democratic,
Freshman Congresswoman
Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez
is hitting back at Speaker Nancy Pelosi.
Pelosi criticized her and
three other far-left Democrats
for voting against that
measure for border funding
that eventually passed
for those facilities,
those detention facilities.
Pelosi told the New York
Times in an interview quote,
"All of these people have
their public whatever
"and their Twitter world.
"But they didn't have any following.
"They're four people and that's
how many votes they got."
So, Ocasio-Cortez taking
to, what else, Twitter,
to fire back, calling Pelosi's decision
to quote, "Blindly trust the White House."
Quote, "A big mistake."
Molly ball, is with me,
National Political Correspondent
for Time.
And Tiffany Cross, Co-Founder
and Managing Editor
of The Beat DC.
Good morning to you both.
Tiffany, let me just begin with you.
I mean, ideologically, these two,
they're in the same party,
but ideologically on this
they could not be more divided.
I do think it's interesting, though,
that Nancy Pelosi has
also said in the midst
of all of this, criticizing the media.
Saying, you know, you're focusing too much
on division in the
party, than on the issue
at the southern border.
We're focusing a lot on the
issue at the southern border.
But, how significant is this divide?
- Well, I take the Pelosi's point,
that I do think there is this, you know,
continual drive that
Democrats are out of step.
But, listen, this is a healthy,
generational shift
happening within the party.
And, quite frankly, I do, I'm not here
to beat up on Nancy
Pelosi, I think that she's,
you know, achieved some
congressional feats
in her tenure, of course.
But I do think, in this instance,
that she did look a bit
out of step with her party.
If you remember, Poppy, at the time
when she was going through campaigning
and trying to be House Speaker again
and Congresswoman Ayanna Pressley,
one of the people who didn't vote for
the border funding bill said,
I'm going to vote for you
but I did not come here to ask
for your permission to lead.
And this is what she
is reckoning with now.
These four women are not
diversity hall decoration
for Congress, but they are
lawmakers intending to legislate
and vote their conscience, rather,
and reflect the views
of their constituency.
This is a major defeat for her because
she's used to being
able to whip her caucus
and keep people in step.
But, as this generational shift happens
you're going to see this kind
of discord on these occasions.
And I don't think that's
a bad thing for the party.
- So Molly, it's interesting the line
that really struck us in
the Dowd piece in the Times.
From Pelosi quote, "If
the left doesn't think
"I'm left enough, so be it."
Will that work for her?
Is that fine or will
she have to answer more
and more calls from the left?
- Well, we'll see.
I think that she's going
to be increasingly tested
by these divisions within the caucus.
We're going to see this week as
the debate heats up over Pentagon funding,
whether she can keep those
Liberal members in the tent.
Her tactic has always been to, sort of,
use the left to triangulate.
Because she identifies as a Liberal.
Because she's from one of
the most Liberal districts
in the country.
Even though she is not nearly, I think,
as Liberal as her
district in San Francisco.
She has always, sort of,
especially since Republicans
have spent hundreds of millions
of dollars portraying her
as the epitome of San
Francisco Liberalism.
She then takes that and says,
well, they call me a Liberal,
I guess I am, that means
that I'm on your side.
But, this is the most we
can get done practically.
I don't think this is really
an ideological division
so much as a tactical one.
And what Speaker Pelosi is saying is,
I understand that you have these ideas
but are you working within the system?
Are you working with in the process?
So she's saying, you may
have support out there
on Twitter or in the real world,
do you have support in the conference?
And that's what we're going to see
is are these Liberals
willing to play hardball
with the leadership?
Are they going to make Nancy
Pelosi's life more difficult?
Because although there
was a lot of complaining
about that border bill, Nancy Pelosi
did get her version through the House.
And then she did get the
Senate bill through the House.
- [Poppy] That's true.
- Can I just push back
really quickly, Poppy?
- Of course, yep.
- I hear you Molly, I completely agree.
But, I do think this
actually is an ideological
and a tactical division
within these women.
They're, all four, women of color
who voted against this bill.
The reality that, I think,
there's trouble reconciling
within this country is, if these
were white babies being treated this way
in these detention facilities.
If these were white women being held
in overcrowded facilities being
told to drink from toilets.
There certainly would be
more of a national outcry.
I think that's so important and resonating
with these four women who said,
we cannot trust this administration.
And there's been continual evidence
of Donald Trump misusing funds.
I mean, we just saw in July 4th.
But as a candidate and as a president
he has misused funds.
So, I think there is something
about these women saying,
why would we blindly trust this man?
Why would we allow ICE
to have more funding.
We just found out today that ICE
is using facial recognition technology.
Well, states haven't
passed laws to allow that.
Undocumented immigrants,
when they signed up
they didn't know that they were turning
their information over to ICE.
I think these are relevant issues.
- You're referencing the
Washington Post reporting
that says that ICE has been
using facial recognition
technology to scan photos at the DMV
of driver's licenses, even of people
not accused of committing crimes.
And that raises a whole host
of other questions, certainly.
Molly, I found this attack,
actually, on Nancy Pelosi
from former Republican, now independent,
Congressman Justin Amash of Michigan.
(emergency alert tone)
- [Announcer] We interrupt this program
to activate the Emergency Alert System
for the Washington, DC
Metropolitan Operational Area
because of a local weather emergency.
- [Female Announcer] The
National Weather Service
in Sterling, Virginia has now extended
the flash flood warning for
the northwestern District of Columbia.
Southern Montgomery County
in central Maryland.
East central Louden
county, Arlington county,
the city of Falls Church and
northeastern Fairfax county
until 1:45 this afternoon.
An emergency management
has reported widespread,
flash flooding across the
are that is still ongoing
even though the heavy rain has ended.
Three to five inches of rain
fell earlier across the area.
Many waterways are still rapidly rising
with ongoing flash flooding.
The flash flood warning is extended now,
through early afternoon.
Some locations that will
experience flooding include:
Arlington, Alexandria,
Bethesda, Reston, Olney,
Herndon, Langley Park,
Vienna, Falls Church,
Lowes Island, Pimmit Hills, Poolesville,
McLean, The American
Legion Bridge, Fort Totten,
Rosslyn, Aspen Hill, Potomac,
North Bethesda and Ashburn.
(emergency alert tones)
- [Poppy] World Cup title
for US Women's Soccer.
Now, their fight at home
is an even bigger one,
a fight for equal pay.
(people cheering)
- I'm Chris Cuomo, let's get after it.
- [Announcer] Tonight, former
Vice President Joe Biden
and his wife Jill join Chris.
A revealing look at the candidate.
- The one thing you cannot say about Joe
is that he's a racist.
- [CNN Announcer] Cuomo Prime
Time, tonight, nine Eastern.
- [Announcer] How do you
gauge the greatness of an SUV?
Is it to carry cargo or
to carry on a legacy?
Its show of strength, or
its sign of intelligence.
In crossing harsh terrain
or breaking new ground.
This is the time to get
an exceptional offer
on the Mercedes of your midsummer dreams
at the Mercedes-Benz
Summer Event, going on now.
Lease the GLA 250 SUV for just 329 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz Summer Event.
Mercedes-Benz, the best or nothing.
- My experience with
USAA has been excellent.
They really appreciate military family
and it really shows.
- With all that USAA offers,
why go with anybody else?
We know their rates are good.
We know that they're always
gonna take care of us.
- It was a instant savings
and I should've changed
a long time ago.
- It was funny, because we would call
another insurance company, they would say,
oh, we can't be USAA.
- We're the Weber family's.
- We're the Tenny's.
- We're the Hail's and
we're USAA members for life.
- [Announcer] Get your USAA
auto insurance quote, today.
- [Woman Announcer] Did you know Congress
is working to end
surprise medical billing?
That's when patients are
hit with medical bills
they thought would be
covered by insurance.
The problem is, big
insurance companies want
a one-size-fits-all approach,
that let's them decide
what they'll pay doctors for your care.
Letting insurance companies decide means
it could be harder for you
to see the best doctors
when you need them the most.
Tell Congress, end surprise billing
and don't let insurance companies
put profits over patients.
Paid for by Physicians for Fair Coverage.
- [Announcer] It's only a matter of time
until your check engine light comes on
or worse yet, your car needs repair.
That could mean a big
surprise auto repair bill.
Those repairs are more
expensive than ever.
A new engine can be over $5,000.
A new transmission over $4,000.
That's why it's so important
you call CarShield today.
CarShield is the number
one auto protection company
in the country.
- I like CarShield because
they were reliable,
they were affordable and
they were trustworthy.
- Well, I think everybody
should have CarShield.
Once your manufacturer's
warranty has expired
there's just no big bills.
We needed repairs,
CarShield was there for us.
- [Announcer] Now it's your turn to get
the peace of mind that
comes with having CarShield.
So, you can worry less about auto repairs.
Call or go online right now
to get CarShield for yourself.
Friendly, knowledgeable,
money-saving representatives
are available 24 hours a day.
So, if your car is 20 years old or newer,
just tell us the make and
model of your car or truck
to get an instant plan quote.
In a matter of minutes you can be covered.
- I was elated that I had CarShield.
I was more than happy.
- There's no fun when you
have a car and it's broken
and you can't pay for it to get it fixed.
- [Announcer] Here's how CarShield works.
When your car needs repair, you take it
to your favorite mechanic
or even your dealer
and CarShield gets them paid directly.
That's why CarShield
is America's number one
auto protection provider.
- CarShield is just the best
thing to take away the fear
that when something is going to go wrong
with your car, because
it will, and CarShield
is gonna be there to back you up.
- My experience with CarShield is that
they absolutely come through,
every time I need them.
- If my car breaks down,
I can count on CarShield
to cover it for me.
CarShield definitely has my back.
- [Announcer] Now it's the
time to make the smart choice
and protect yourself from
sky high auto repair bills.
Call now for a free and
instant protection plan quote.
It's only a matter of time
until repairs are needed.
And once your car breaks
down, it's too late.
Call 1-800-915-9597.
That's 1-800-915-9597.
- Introducing Nutrisystem's July 4th sale.
Save 50%, yes, 50%.
- [Announcer] Lose up to 13 pounds
and seven inches in your first month.
Order your 28-day plan and get one week
of high protein shakes with probiotics
to help shrink your belly free.
- And there's even a money-back guarantee.
- [Announcer] Save 50% off every program.
- Grab this special offer right now
and start losing today.
- [Announcer] Go online
or call 877-314-FIT8,
right now, to save 50%.
- [Male Announcer]
Closed captioning brought
to you by mesobook.com.
- Mesothelioma is all we do.
For over 10 years we
have offered a free book
on mesothelioma.
Call 1-800-259-9374.
(upbeat music)
- All right, this just in to CNN.
New York Governor, Andrew
Cuomo, has just signed a law
that would allow Congress to get a hold
of President Trump's state tax returns.
Of course, this comes
amid the escalating fight
with top administration
officials and Congress,
trying to get the president's
federal tax returns.
We'll see how this develops.
- Equal pay.
- Well fans chanted equal pay as
the Women's National Team
received their World Cup medals
after their second straight win on Sunday.
The team is suing the US Soccer
Federation over their pay
and their star is speaking out
about that suit this morning.
Andy Scholes joins us with more.
So much to celebrate there
Andy, such a big win.
But I would argue the bigger fight now,
for them, is at home.
- Yeah, that could be true, Poppy.
But I'll tell you what,
if there was ever a team
that symbolized talking the
talk and then walking the walk
it is certainly this US
Women's National Team.
What we just witnessed from them was just
an incredible performance.
They had so much going on off the field.
The fight for equal pay,
Megan Rapinoe's back and forth
with President Trump.
But this team's still
able to put it all aside
and go out there and prove, once again,
that they are the best team in the world.
Team USA beating the
Netherlands, two to nothing,
yesterday in the final.
They're on their way back
to the US, right now,
after leaving France earlier this morning.
Here's a pretty cool
pic they took together
before boarding their plane.
They're gonna arrive at Newark Airport
at about 4:15 Eastern.
They're gonna have a parade
Wednesday morning in New York.
Before leaving France, Rapinoe was asked,
how their dominant performance will affect
the US Federation's argument against them
in their Equal Pay lawsuit.
- It's not good for
them, is it. (laughing)
I mean, I think obviously, it's huge.
I think we've been a
little shy to say that,
you know, putting so much
pressure on ourselves
because I think we have
a case no matter what.
Obviously, we brought the lawsuit.
But this just, you know, sort
of blows it out of the water.
It's like, is it even about that anymore?
Or is it just, kind of
about doing the right thing.
I think the Federation
is in a unique position
to, you know, kind of ride
this wave of good fortune
and get on board, and
hopefully, set things right
for the future.
- Yeah, the players and
the US Soccer Federation
will head to mediation
sometime soon, over pay.
Over the past three
years, the women's team
has made more revenue than the men,
despite being paid less.
That being said, the men didn't
make the World Cup last year
and the money difference in
the World Cup is staggering.
The Men's World Cup in Russia
last year made $6,000,000,000
in revenue and paid out
400 million to the teams.
The Women's World Cup, meanwhile,
is expected to generate
only about 130 million in revenue, total.
Paying out 30 million to the teams.
There's no question, the women's team
is more successful than
the men here in the US.
We all know their names,
they sell more jerseys.
But, right now, there's still just
so much more money in men's soccer.
We're gonna have to wait and see, Poppy,
if the US Soccer
Federation decides to give
the women a pay raise.
They certainly deserve it, after
a fourth World Cup title.
But in the past, the Federation has argued
that the women's and men's
teams are separate organizations
that perform services for US Soccer.
They have separate collective
bargaining agreements
and they have separate budgets
that take into account different revenue
that the team's generate.
- Yeah well, you also have to be able
to see the women's games
in more places, Andy.
I mean, there have been networks
that have pulled their games, et cetera.
So, come on.
All right, before you go, let's talk about
the 15 year old tennis phenom
Coco Gauff, back in action.
Right now, playing in
Wimbledon this morning.
How is she doing and
just big picture, I mean,
for so many of us, that
aren't big tennis fans,
she came out of the blue, superstar.
- She certainly did and she is definitely
a superstar in the making, Poppy.
But right now, this
morning, not looking good
for her Wimbledon future.
She lost the first set
to world number one,
Simona Halep, 6-3, down
5-2 in the second set.
But she was actually
in a similar situation
when she made that big comeback on Friday.
But Coco has just really
become a crowd favorite
at Wimbledon, after becoming the youngest
to make it to the round of 16 in 28 years.
She doesn't turn 16 till March.
Just an incredible, incredible run.
I mean, Poppy, when you were 15,
could imagine doing something like this?
I know I sure couldn't.
- I don't know what I was doing at 15,
nothing close to that, she is remarkable.
Rooting for her.
Andy Scholes, thank you.
- All right.
- Soon, president Trump
will give a speech,
as in, just a few hours from now.
Touting his record on the environment.
Really?
We'll talk about it.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(wind howling)
♪ I want it that way ♪
- I can't believe it.
- That Carl brought his karaoke machine?
♪ Nothin' but a heartache ♪
- No, I can't believe how easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
my car insurance with GEICO.
♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ I never wanna hear you say ♪
- Go Kevin.
(wind howling)
(door slamming)
♪ I want it that way ♪
- [Announcer] Believe it,
GEICO could save you 15%
or more on car insurance.
♪ Born to be wild ♪
- [Announcer] Let them move
the way they were born to
in new Pampers Cruisers 360 Fit.
With it's ultra stretchy waistband
and adaptive 360 fit.
New Pampers Pampers Cruisers 360 Fit.
- [Male Announcer] Here's another reason
to join T-Mobile.
Unlimited data, with
taxes and fees included.
No surprises on your bill.
And here's another reason to join,
bring in your discount
(chiming) and we'll match it.
That's right, T-Mobile,
we'll match your discount.
(T-Mobile chimes ringing)
(water splashing)
(Birds chirping)
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Corey is living
with metastatic breast cancer.
Which is breast cancer that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking IBRANCE
with an aromatase inhibitor
which is for post-menopausal
women or for men
with HR+ or HER2- metastatic breast cancer
as the first hormonal-based therapy.
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease
progression, versus letrozole.
Patients taking IBRANCE can develop
low white blood cell counts,
which may cause serious infections
that can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE, tell your doctor
if you have fever, chills,
or other signs of infection.
Liver or kidney problems, are pregnant,
breastfeeding or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects
include, low red blood cell
and low platelet counts,
infections, tiredness
nausea, sore mouth, abnormalities
in liver blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning or loss, vomiting,
rash and loss of appetite.
Corey calls it her new normal
because a lot has changed
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about IBRANCE,
the number one prescribed,
FDA-approved, oral combination treatment
for HR+, HER2-, MBC.
- Today you are going to become a cook.
- So, how do we do it?
- Let's just follow the directions.
It's like a life hack.
I can't believe we made this.
- It's really good.
- [Announcer] Go to Hellofresh.com
and join the number one meal kit company.
Use code TV80 to get $80 off
Hello Fresh, get cooking.
- In one week, a lot
will happen in your life.
Wrinkles just won't.
Neutrogena Rapid Wrinkle Repair's
derm-proven Retinol, works
so fast, it takes only one week
to reveal younger looking skin.
Neutrogena.
(upbeat music)
- Today's Best Western,
what does that mean?
♪ Best day of my life ♪
- [Announcer] With Rewards
points that never expire
you get free nights fast.
Now, get a $20 Best Western
gift card after your first day.
Book now at BestWestern.com.
- [Male Announcer] After transforming
to meet the challenges of a
digital world, never stop.
After engineering 3-D imaging technologies
that help doctors quickly
diagnose disease, never stop.
And after advancing drug
delivery technology expertise
to help in the fight
against cancer, never stop.
And we'll never stop improving the future
by building on our core innovations
and over 80 years of experience.
Never stop.
Fujifilm, value from innovation.
(orchestral thunder)
- [Announcer] Former Special
Counsel Robert Muller
testifies before Congress, live.
The Mueller hearing, Wednesday, July 17th.
Coverage begins at eight a.m. on CNN.
- Hiring was always a huge challenge.
Endless hours on job sites,
with not a lot to show for it.
Then, I found ZipRecruiter.
They figured out hiring.
I post my job, they
put it all over the web
and they send me the right people.
Because their technology is smart.
ZipRecruiter often sends me
the right person in 24 hours.
- [Announcer] ZipRecruiter,
the smartest way to hire.
Try it for free at ziprecruiter.com/Reach.
♪ Limu Emu ♪
- [Announcer] And Doug.
- What do all these people
have in common, Limu?
(paper shuffling)
Exactly, nothing, they're
completely different people.
That's why they need
customized car insurance
from Liberty Mutual, they'll
only pay for what they need.
(change jingling)
Yes, and they could save a ton.
You've done it again Limu.
- [Announcer] Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty, Liberty, Liberty ♪
- I'm Farai Sevenzo in
Nairobi, this is CNN.
(orchestral thunder)
- All right, so in just a few hours,
president Trump will give a speech.
As the White House puts it, quote,
"To recognize his administration's
environmental leadership
"and America's leading role in the world."
But his speech would follow major steps
in his administration, to reverse
over 80 environmental regulations
put in place under the
Obama administration.
Let's talk about the facts here.
Bill Weir, our Chief Climate
Correspondent is with me.
Also Christine Todd Whitman, a Republican,
former EPA Administrator under
the George W. Bush administration
and former governor of New Jersey.
Good morning to you both.
All right, so we're going to hear from
the administration on this today.
And we'll get to, sort
of, why they're doing
this now, in a moment.
But let me just outline for everyone
what this administration's own EPA said
in a report that came out in April.
Here are the things that
are happening because
of the climate crisis and emergency.
Hurricane storm intensity, frequency
and duration will increase.
More intense droughts,
warmer temperatures,
causing larger wildfires
and longer fire seasons.
And, they warned, this is
the president's own EPA,
to anticipate a combination of impacts,
floods and fires which may be intensified
because of the changing climate.
From what you've seen, the
evidence, not the rhetoric,
is the Trump administration taking
this seriously enough, at all?
- No, not at all.
And they're rolling back regulations
in a whole lot of other areas that
are making people lives less healthy.
They're a threat to us in
so many different ways.
The climate crisis is just one of them
and that's of course the
huge, 800 pound gorilla.
Pretending it doesn't
exist doesn't stop it,
that doesn't make it go away.
- Even, no matter what
you say in a speech.
- Absolutely.
- Here, in a few hours
some of what's been rolled back, Bill,
include, obviously, pulling out of
the Paris climate agreement,
that's a huge deal.
Lowering the car emission standards
that had been increased, right,
to stop so much pollution.
Weakening the Clean Power Plan
from the Obama administration.
Eliminating the EPA panel on air pollution
and opening up Anwar, which you've done
a lot of reporting on, in the Arctic.
- Yeah, you know the
president is old enough
to remember when you could
taste the air in Los Angeles.
And when the Cuyahoga
River in Ohio was on fire
it was so polluted.
And today, you can swim the
Cuyahoga, it's beautiful.
And you can go to LA and see
the San Gabriel Mountains.
But that that didn't happen on accident.
- Right.
- By accident.
It didn't happen on its own.
It happened when Nixon signed
the Clear Air and Water Act.
And then 40 years of deliberate lawmaking
to grind this thing out, to get us where
you can stand and say, hey,
isn't the air really clear.
New Zealand blows us away.
Sweden has more beautiful cities.
But what's lost in this clean air,
clean water today
messaging, is that he should
be saying, step to the microphone and say,
when Barron is my age, America is gonna be
a completely, life as we know it
will be completely different.
- [Poppy] Because it
is about our children.
- It is.
- It's about the future
and he has a young child
as you bring up.
So listen to, obviously, the president
has touted this and
talked about America's air
and water as being at a
record clean, his words.
And then the Vice President, Mike Pence,
on with Jake Tapper just a few weeks ago
made this argument, listen.
- America has the cleanest
air and water in the world.
We'll continue to
- That's not true
- use market forces.
- We don't have
the cleanest air and water in the world.
- I, I.
- We don't. (chuckling)
Well, you get back to me with
some statistics that show it.
- We're making progress on
reducing carbon emissions.
- I mean, Jake laughed
because it is laughable.
Because it's just not true.
What are your concerns ahead of the speech
when the administration is putting out,
just blatant untruths
about the environment.
- My concern is that people seem to take
what he says and say,
okay, he may be lying.
He may not be telling the whole truth
but we don't really care.
We've got to care.
This is the moment when we really need
to care about this and
it is about our children
and our grandchildren.
It's about the future and about
making our lives healthier.
Making our our economy
greater, which we can do
and we've done it over
time, as you pointed out,
when we started the EPA
with the Clean Air Act,
the Clean Water, Safe Drinking Water.
We saw the population grow exponentially.
We saw the real GDP more than double.
We saw our energy use
climb and yet we were able
to grow our economy at
extraordinary rates.
So it's not an either/or thing
and we have got to get
over this idea that it is
and somehow doing away with regulation
is gonna make everything happy.
- I think that's a good point and Bill,
you've done so much reporting on this.
I mean, it doesn't have to be the case
that protecting the
environment hurts business.
It means you transform business.
- Absolutely.
As the governor points out, we didn't go
into a 40-year recession
when we started worrying
about breathable air,
those sort of things.
But the other thing that, you
know, the big picture story
that we're just not wired as
human beings to worry about.
We don't think in long
earth-long time frames.
We think of if, that noise
behind that (audio dropping)
is going to eat me, right.
So, you don't think that.
But if you take a step back and realize
that every 2.7 seconds, a
piece of the Arctic ice,
about the size of a football
field, turns to water.
It's been that way for 40 years.
So, again, Barron Trump will not get
a 30-year mortgage in Miami,
because it will change
the actual, physical
topography of our land.
- The administration we hear, Bill, a lot,
talk about natural gas and
the push for natural gas
and replacing coal,
parts of coal with that
and how that, you know,
essentially, solves things.
It helps, right, but it
doesn't at all address
the big issue, does it?
- Well, everything's cleaner
than coal. (chuckling)
We could burn whales
again and it's be cleaner,
it'd be an improvement over coal.
But it's still exacerbating the problem.
And the governor can back
me up on, just the numbers.
As solar and wind has actually increased
and gotten cheaper, it
hasn't replaced fossil fuels.
We just have a more voracious appetite,
so we're burning everything.
Solar, wind and.
- Nuclear.
- Nuclear should be part
of this conversation.
- I think the transition, is nuclear,
is what we've gotta look at.
Because we've got these nuclear reactors
that produce no regulated
pollutants or greenhouse gases
while they're producing power.
And we seem to be closing them down
which is what, I think, is the problem.
We're not gonna build any
more new ones, big ones.
But small, modular reactors, the rest of
the world's going this way.
We could create an
enormous number of jobs.
They'd be really good for the economy.
That's the new wave,
along with the renewables.
And until the renewables, as Bill said,
get to be base power,
not just peak shaving,
so they're on 24/7, then great,
then we can go with that.
- Governor Whitman, thank you.
Bill Weir, thank you so much.
We'll be watching.
Again, the president's
gonna give this address
in just a few hours.
You should watch it or
read the entire thing.
(dramatic orchestral music)
This just in, American
tennis phenom, Coco Gauff's,
magical run at Wimbledon has ended.
She just lost in straight sets
to former number one
ranked player Simona Halep.
The 15 year old was the youngest player
to make it to the round of 16 in 28 years.
Congrats to her for making it so far.
I think we're gonna be watching her
for many, many years to come.
All right, minutes from
now the FBI and US Attorney
will be giving a press conference.
They are announcing really serious,
sex trafficking charges against
billionaire Jeffrey Epstein.
He's accused of running
a sex trafficking ring,
sexually abusing dozens of underage girls.
Of course, you'll see that
press conference live here
in just a few minutes.
This is critically
important, stay with CNN.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(gentle piano music)
- [Announcer] Parents have a
way of imagining the worst.
Especially when your
easily distracted teenager
has the car.
At Subaru we're taking
on distracted driving
with sensors that alert you
when your eyes are off the road.
(tires squealing)
The all-new Subaru Forester.
The safest Forester ever.
- When I book at Hilton.com
I got to select my room
from the floorplan, free Wi-Fi
and the price match guarantee.
- So, with Hilton, there is no catch?
- Yeah, the only catch
is, I'm never leaving.
No, I'm serious, I live here now.
- [Announcer] Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton price match guarantee.
♪ Limu Emu ♪
- [Announcer] And Doug.
- Exactly, Liberty Mutual
customizes your car insurance
so you only pay for what you need.
- Nice, but what's up with your partner?
- Oh, we just spend all
day telling everyone
how we customize car insurance because
no two people are alike.
So, Limu gets a little confused
when he sees another bird
that looks exactly like him.
He'll figure it out.
- [Announcer] Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty, Liberty, Liberty ♪
- This is one of the most
important days of my life
and you know who wasn't
invited, mosquitos.
That's why we've always Orkin.
Carl's so good, it's like
he's never really left.
- Ladies, I've got lavender and coconut.
- Isn't me the cutest?
- Smile.
- Here's what's up, look at me,
yes, real people really do win.
- Oh my gosh.
- I'm here with Publishers
Clearing House and we're ready.
- To make you a winner.
- It's real.
- You could win five grand a week,
week after week, for life.
The van is all ready to go.
- And someone is going to win big.
- So, what you waiting for?
August 30th you could
win yourself five grand
a week, for life.
- Are you serious?
- You gotta be in it to win it.
Five grand a week for life.
So enter now at pch.com.
- last year, millions of
homeowners used HomeAdvisor
to get matched with top
rated pros for small projects
like fixing a garage door
or unclogging a drain.
But you can also use
HomeAdvisor to find trusted pros
for bigger projects, like building a deck
or remodeling your kitchen.
For projects big and small, HomeAdvisor
is always free to use.
Compare prices, read reviews
and find the best local pros
at homeadvisor.com or
download the free app.
♪ HomeAdvisor ♪
(doorbell ringing)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(glass crashing)
- [Announcer] Play it cool
and escape heartburn fast
with new Tums Chewy
Bites cooling sensation.
♪ Tum Tum Tum Tum Tums ♪
- I was so anxious to do
one line from the script.
You complete me.
There were times that I
thought is this too cheesy?
And I told Tom that.
And he said, just give me a shot at it.
- You complete me.
- I look around, everybody's crying.
The grizzled guys holding
cable are like. (sniffling)
I was like, I think it's
gonna work. (laughing)
- [Announcer] The movies we love
and the stories behind them.
Sunday's on CNN.
- If something happened to you
what would happen to them?
Their home, their education, their future.
You need life insurance and chances are
SelectQuote can help you get it for less
than a dollar a day.
- [Announcer] SelectQuote found Jacob, 40
a $500,000 policy for only $19 a month.
And SelectQuote found his wife Wendy
a $500,000 policy for only $17 a month.
- Our secret?
At SelectQuote we
aggressively comparison shop
up to 10 highly rated
companies to find you
the company with.