- Five of the top presidential candidates
are sharing the same stage tonight
for town halls with young adults.
And students who say
that they plan to vote
in their states' primaries and caucuses.
And they are right here
in the audience with us.
We've already heard from
Senators Amy Klobuchar,
Elizabeth Warren and Bernie Sanders.
And next hour we're gonna hear
from Mayor Pete Buttigieg.
But right now it's time to
welcome to this very stage
Senator Kamala Harris of California.
(audience applauds)
- Hey guys, hi, hi.
- Good to see you.
- Good to be, have a seat.
- Thank you.
- Wow they're happy to see you.
- Hi, good to see you guys.
- Now let's get to it because we want you
to get as much out the
next hour both of you.
- That sounds great.
- All of you as possible
so let's start with what's dominating
the news right now.
And You know that's the fallout
from the Mueller report.
- [Kamala] Yes.
- We have a question from
her name is Karla Alvarado,
she's right there to the right.
And Karla is a senior
at Harvard University
from Massachusetts, Karla.
- Good evening Senator Harris.
Thank you for joining us this evening.
In light of Mueller's report,
do you believe the Democrats in Congress
should reconsider their
position on impeachment?
- Well it depends on who you're talking to
and what their position is.
But here's how I feel about it
and thank you for the question Karla.
Look, for those of us
who have been following
the investigation and have
seen any part of that report.
It is very clear that there
is a lot of good evidence
pointing to obstruction
and obstruction of justice.
And I believe very strongly,
first of all let me
just be very clear about the table set.
I believe that we need to
get rid of this president
that's why I'm running for
to become president of the United States.
So that is part of the
premise obviously of my point.
But I think we have very
good reason to believe
that there is an investigation
that has been conducted,
which has produced evidence
that tells us that this
president and his administration
engaged in obstruction of justice.
I believe congress should
take the steps towards impeachment.
(audience applauds)
But I wanna say this because
it doesn't end there,
I also wanna say this.
I am also a realist and
when I look at what has been
happening over the two
years and some months
that I've been in the
United States Senate.
I have also witnessed folks
in the United States Congress
and in particular in the GOP.
Who have been presented with
many reasons to push back
against this president and they have not.
And when we look at the
impeachment process.
There will be what happens in the House,
an investigation that takes place.
I think we can be pretty
sure that it looks like that
is very likely to happen.
And then it's gonna go over
to the Senate and in the House
there needs to be a vote by a
majority, a simple majority.
And then it's gonna
come over to the senate.
And I've not seen any evidence
since I've been in the
United States Senate.
That the United States Senate
and the Republicans hold the majority.
I've not seen any evidence to suggest
that they will weigh on the facts
instead of on partisan adherence
to being protective of this president.
And that's what concerns me
and what will be the eventual outcome.
So we have to be realistic about
what might be the end result.
But that doesn't mean the
process should not take hold.
- All right thank you Senator.
Let's talk about you cause
a lot of the young folks.
A lot of the students here
at the Harvard Institute of Politics.
They're concerned about how
gun violence might affect them
or family members, someone
who's close to them.
On that topic is Ben Bernier,
he's standing right there.
He's a student at the
University of New Hampshire
studying history, he is
from Massachusetts, Ben.
- Thank you, thank you Senator.
- Hi Ben.
- As a future educator I'm really bothered
that public schools are being
targets for mass shootings.
Two days ago was the 20th anniversary
of the Columbine Massacre.
But still two decades later
no major gun control
legislation has been passed.
So my question is as president,
how will you go about
keeping our schools safe and
keeping guns out of the hands
of those who should not have them?
- Thank you Ben and I'm
sure that there are plenty
of students here who while
you were in high school,
even middle school,
that you had to participate
in a drill, right.
Where you were convened and
your teachers taught you
about how you need to go run in a closet
'cause there maybe a mass
shooter roaming the hallways
at your school.
And in our America that
should never have to happen.
Conversations take place--
(audience applauds)
every night.
Conversations take place
every night between students
and their parents.
Why do these things have to happen?
Why do we have to have a drill like that?
To which of course the response
is because there are people
in Washington DC supposed leaders.
Who have failed to have the courage
to reject a false choice.
Which suggests you're either in favor
of the Second Amendment
or you wanna take everyone's guns away.
Supposed leaders in
Washington DC who have failed
to have the courage to recognize.
You know what you wanna
go hunting that's fine.
But we need reasonable gun
safety laws in this country
starting with universal background checks
and a renewal of the assault weapon ban.
But they have failed to
have the courage to act
so Ben here's my response to you.
Upon being elected I will give
the United States Congress
100 days to get their act
together and have the courage
to pass reasonable gun safety laws.
And if they fail to do it, then
I will take executive action
and specifically what I will do
is put in place a requirement
that for anyone who sells
more than five guns a year
they are required to do background checks
when they sell those guns.
I will require that for any
gun dealer that breaks the law
the ATF take their license.
And by the way ATF, Alcohol
Tobacco and Firearms.
Well the ATF has being
a lot of the A and the T
but not much of the F
and we need to fix that.
And then--
(audience applauds)
On the third piece cause
none of us have been sleeping
over the last two years.
Part of what has happened under
the current administration
is they took fugitives off
the list of prohibited people.
I'd put them back on the
list meaning that fugitives
from justice should not be
able to purchase a handgun,
or any kind of weapon.
So that's what I'd do.
- [Don] Will this be
your first executive action as president?
- Well it depends on what else happens
that'd be after 100 days.
Let's see what happens
in the first 100 days.
- All right, fair enough.
Angela Garrazzo is here
and she is a freshman
at Saint Anselm College studying
International Relations.
She is from New Hampshire, Angela.
- Good evening Senator my
question is as a college student
with over $25,000 of debt
in my first year alone.
What will you do to alleviate
the financial burdens
of the student debt crisis?
Do you support initiatives
such as free college,
loan protective legislation
or student repayment plans?
- Yeah Angela, and listen,
the students in New Hampshire
are among the top five in the country
with student loan debt.
And it is absolutely unconscionable
that we have students
in America who are in absolute fear,
about the debt that they
will owe upon graduation.
And I have met and know so many students
who are making decisions
about their career
based on their fear that they may not
be able to pay their bills.
I know so many students who have graduated
who are making decisions
about whether or not to have a family.
Based on the burden of
their student loan debt
and being concerned about
whether they're gonna actually
be able to get through the month.
We cannot afford to
have a system like this
especially for young people who have made
an investment of their
time and their resources.
Because they actually want an education
to live a productive life
and contribute to our
society and be leaders.
So here's what I'd do specifically
I do support debt-free college.
I also believe that what we
need to do is we need to allow
students to refinance
your student loan debt.
And in particular I am supporting
an initiative that would
allow you to refinance
your student loan debt
such that it would be on par
with the federal lending amounts.
So for example if you,
probably none of you here,
but any of your older
brothers and sisters.
If you took out student loans
between the years of about
2006 through 2013 the
interest rate was about 7%.
What I am proposing is
regardless of the interest rate
at the time that you took
out your student loans,
that upon repayment it
would have to be at 3.5%.
The other thing is this, part of the issue
is in terms of repayment.
There is no connection between
what you owe and your income.
So what I would be requiring
is that there would be
a robust process by which
income-based repayment
would be the norm.
And finally, let's look at
the fact that for all of you
and all of anybody who has
applied for financial aid.
That is an awful process.
You guys know what I'm
talking about all those pages
you can barely get through that form.
(audience applauds)
And so part of what we need to
do is simplify that process.
But we have got to do a
better job in this country
because I look at something
like for example teachers.
I've been spending a lot of time.
I think a lot about education in terms of
every aspect of it from student loans,
to what we need to do to pay
our teachers their value.
And the number of teachers
who have left the profession of teaching,
'cause they can't afford to
pay off their student loans.
Right now we're looking at
actually a deficit of teachers
based on the number of students
that we need to actually
teach and the few teachers we
have especially rural areas.
So it's a big issue and it
crosses a lot of subjects.
- Well let me jump in
here because if students,
I mean teachers can pay their loans.
Elizabeth Warren is here as you know.
She said that she supports
student loan forgiveness
for 42 million Americans.
- Yeah.
- Would you go that far,
do you support that?
- Well I support anything that
is about reducing the debt
of student loans and I think
that's an important conversation to have.
- Okay fair enough.
Let's move on now, Ryan Wilson
is here, Ryan is a sophomore
at Harvard studying
Neuroscience in California
and a supporter of Julian Castro, Ryan.
- Hi, good evening Senator Harris.
My name is Ryan and I'm
a constituent of yours
from Orange country California.
In a January town hall, when
asked about your approach
to universal health care,
you acknowledged that you'd support
eliminating private insurers in favor
of a single payer health
insurance program.
How do you respond to the 74% of Americans
who wish to have the option to
keep their private insurers?
- Well I support Medicare for all
and I support it for a number of reasons.
That include the fact that
there are a lot of people
in our country who simply do
not have access to healthcare
'cause they cannot afford it.
And that's unconscionable
and I actually believe it's a moral issue.
And it is a sign of weather or not
we are gonna be a civil society
to determine are people gonna
have access to healthcare
simply because they can afford it.
When in fact that should be
a right and not a privilege
of the few who can afford it.
That is the value with which
I bring to this discussion.
I will also say this on the
issue of this whole dynamic
about access to private insurance.
Yeah of course private insurance
you can get supplemental
insurance and all that.
But let's not be duped
by a messaging campaign
that has been waged for years
by the insurance companies.
To have you into believing
that you need to defend them,
you need to defend yourself.
You know what 91% of the
doctors are in Medicare.
So the idea and the suggestion
they're trying to make to you
is really a false one.
You will be able to have your doctor.
91% of them are in the Medicare system.
And I'll tell you another thing
and it's a personal story.
My mother who, my mother
was all of five feet tall,
if you ever met her
you would thought she was seven feet tall.
She was an incredible woman.
She had two goals in her life.
She was a breast cancer researcher.
Her goal was to end breast cancer
and raise her two daughters.
Well she got cancer
and she ultimately
passed away from cancer.
But if you have ever had
the unfortunate experience
of going through the healthcare system
with someone who has an acute illness.
I'm gonna tell you what that is.
It is having a doctor say to you
have you heard of the
term anticipatory grief.
Which you hadn't heard before
but when you hear it
it makes perfect sense.
Which means you're
starting already to grieve
the loss of someone that is still around.
You have the experience of
going in and out of hospitals
helping someone who is frail
and weak in and out of cars
to get into a hospital.
You look at medical charts
and sometimes the medicine
jives sometimes it doesn't.
Sometimes people are paying attention to
this is the medication
that causes drowsiness.
They don't want, or pain
that they can't bear.
You go through the
process of worrying about
is there something I can
cook that will make you
be able to eat and hold down.
You go through the process of
being concerned that somebody
who is on chemotherapy are there clothes.
Can I get you something that's
soft enough that you can wear
that will not irritate your skin.
Now thankfully our mother had Medicare,
but for people who are
going through this process,
which they are every day in America.
For them to also have to be
concerned about how they're
going to pay that bill is unconscionable.
And that's how I feel about this subject.
Cost should not be the
barrier to receiving the care
that will relieve you of pain
or help improve your quality of life.
And we've got to get this
right that's how I feel.
- So you mentioned the insurance
companies you don't feel
like you have to defend
the insurance companies?
- No I don't have to.
- So the bill that you
co-sponsored it would effectively
eliminate private insurance.
Is there room for private insurance in a?
- No, of course there is,
for supplemental insurance absolutely.
- For companies, for
private insurance companies,
there's room in your
administration for that.
- Yeah.
- Okay, but listen in this bill.
- But Don I think that it's
really important to talk
about the goal.
Right, I mean we can talk
about the intermediate steps.
But the goal has to be
and we all have to agree
access to healthcare is a right
and should be thought of as a right
and pubic policy should create it.
Such that it is a real
right and not a privilege
for those who can afford it.
And it's one of the
biggest issues impacting
American families right now.
I'm traveling this country
it's one of the biggest issues.
The number of people who
sit down and make decisions
about whether they're gonna
have access to healthcare
or not based on money, you would shocked.
One out of four diabetes
patients in our country
cannot afford their insulin.
There is a drug that helps save a life
if there have been an overdose of opioids.
And that drug can cost up
$4,000, that's unconscionable.
- Listen but to be clear this
bill that you co-sponsored
essentially phases out private insurance
for four years, in four years.
- I don't think that's right.
- That's what the studies show
that it would phase out private insurance.
- Which bill, I'm actually supporting?
- The bill that you co-sponsored.
- Medicare for all?
- Yes, would co-sponsored
with Bernie Sanders,
Medicare for all would effectively
eliminate private insurance.
It would essentially phase out
private insurance companies.
- As the main source but there
would still be supplemental.
There'd still be access
to supplemental insurance
- Okay, all right.
- For whatever is not covered
but let's be clear about it.
Medicare for all under the
plan that I am supporting
will extend coverage.
So whereas right now it
does not cover dental,
vision, hearing aids.
Under the plan, Medicare for
all it will cover those needs
will be covered, there
will an extension of it.
Including mental health
services, including what we need
to do better around women
having greater access
to reproductive health care.
- All right, now the Green New Deal.
(audience applauds)
- Yes.
- The Green New Deal,
everyone wants to hear,
wants to know about that.
Max Ratner is originally
from Massachusetts.
He is now a student at Saint
Anselm College right here.
Last summer he interned
for Senator Ed Markey.
Max what's your question?
- Senator Harris thank you
for taking my question.
- Thank you Max.
- The Green New Deal is not
a law but rather a memorandum
that has no actual legislative effect.
It's been characterized as
expensive, divides democrats
and has no chance of
passing through congress
in it's current state.
Why do you support it?
- I support it because I to my core know
that the climate crisis is representing
an existential threat to
who we are as human beings.
We have had supposed leaders
who are buying science
and pushing science fiction
instead of science fact.
And this is to our collective
peril if we don't take
this matter seriously
with a sense of urgency.
Why I support the Green New
Deal is because it does that.
It puts timelines in effect,
it appreciates that we need
to take this seriously
and the clock is ticking
every day on this issue.
And every day we fail to act,
will be to our collective consequence.
The UN has already said
over the next 12 years
if we don't get this straight
there will be severe consequence.
And this is within our ability
to do something about it.
Listen, families are impacted by this.
You know children, seniors we
all need to drink clean air,
drink clean water and breathe clean air.
And you know don't drink the air.
(laughs)
You look at farmers,
farmers are impacted
by this climate change.
You can look at fire
fighters in California
who are impacted by climate change.
Across the board people
are being impacted by this.
Let's also look at the fact
that we have in so many states
great work that is happening.
That is actually
contributing to the economy
around an investment
in renewable energies.
The bureau of labor statistics
came out with a list
last year of the top 20 jobs
that are gonna see the
greatest amount of growth
in our country over the next 10 years.
Number one and number two,
installation and maintenance
of wind turbines and solar paneling.
Let's look at it in the
context of what we know
to be true about water.
Water is a precious and
diminishing resource on our planet.
When you look at what's happening
around shifting populations
around the globe,
climate change is one of the main factors
in what is happening.
There was a time and still to this day
where we're fighting wars over oil.
In a short matter of time guys,
we're gonna be fighting wars over water.
Part of what we can do with
the Green New Deal is have
a sense of urgency on all these matters.
Including the precious nature of water
and what we need to do to
be smarter on public policy.
I think that for example
that we need to have really
diversify public policy on water.
With an equal emphasis on
recycling, on conservation,
on capture of water, storage
of water, desalination.
We need to invest in electric cars.
We need to reduce
greenhouse gas emissions.
All of that is in the Green New Deal.
And you know the greatest thing about it
that I'm really enjoying.
It it causing these
conversations to happen
around our country in a way
they've not been in the last few years.
And hopefully everyone is understanding
that so much of the harm
we are doing to our planet
is caused by us as human beings.
And the solutions will be
because we change our behaviors
without much requirement
of change to lifestyle.
And it will be urgent in terms
of the work we need to do
and the approach we need to
have, but we can see success.
We've seen it in California.
In California we made a decision
that we would go back
to the 1990s standards
in terms of emissions by the year 2020
and we've already met those goals.
This can happen, we can do it
but there has to be leadership
in our country and that
is one of the main reasons
we need a new president
of the United States.
- All right, so speaking of air and water
why don't we take a a breather.
- Okay.
- And get a sip of water,
we're gonna be right back with
more of CNNs special Democratic
presidential town hall event.
Make sure you stay with us.
(audience applauds)
- Shaving has been difficult for me.
I have very sensitive
skin I get ingrown hairs
so it's a daunting task.
(vibrant violin music)
Oh I love it, it's a great razor.
It has that fence in the middle,
it gives a nice smooth shave
just stopping that irritation
that burn that I get.
It's really life changing (laughs)
(peaceful piano music)
- Here comes the rain.
(horn honks)
What's that girl?
(engine revs)
Flo needs help?
Take me to her.
We're coming, Flo!
Why aren't we taking roads?
Flo!
- Oh you made it, do you
have change for a dollar?
- This was the emergency?
(engine revs)
Yes I was busy.
- [Narrator] 24 hour road side assistance
from America's number
one motorcycle insurer.
You know I think you're my best friend.
You don't have to say I'm
your best friend that's okay.
(upbeat drum music)
- [Narrator] Everyday visionaries
are creating the future.
So every day we put our latest technology
and unrivaled network to work.
The United States Postal Service
makes more eCommerce deliveries to homes
than anyone else in the country.
Because the future only
happens with people who really
know how to deliver it.
♪ Woo hoo hoo I feel
my temperature rising ♪
♪ Help me I'm flaming ♪
♪ I must be a hundred and nine ♪
- [Narrator] Applebee's
bigger bolder grill combos
now that's eating good
in the neighborhood.
- With Samuel Adams we were
always looking for the best
hops out of 150,000 acres
of hops in the world.
These 16 are the best of the best.
I can taste your middle fruit hops
in every glass of Boston lager.
- [Narrator] The right gear matters.
Introducing the all new 2019 Ford Ranger.
It's the right gear.
With a terrain management system for this.
A bash plate for that
and electronic locking
rear differential for yeah this.
Heading to the supermarket, get any truck.
Heading out here, get the Ford Ranger.
The only adventure gear built Ford tough.
- [Narrator] Doctor Sanjay
Gupta voyages through
one of the darkest coldest
countries in the world, Norway.
- How come I'm the only one that's cold?
- [Narrator] And finds some
of the happiest people.
What's their secret?
Chasing Life, Saturday
May 4th at nine eastern.
- Great, another wireless ad.
So many of them are full this
complicated tricky language
about their network and offers
and blah blah blah blah blah.
Look, Sprint's gonna do things differently
and let you decide for yourself.
They're offering a new 100%
total satisfaction guarantee.
Try it out and see the savings.
If you don't love it get your money back.
See, simple.
Now Sprint's unlimited plan
comes with one of the newest
phones included for just $35 a month.
So switch now.
(light-hearted piano music)
- What's good Josh, it's Deshawn.
Man I know what's you're going through.
You know sometimes you get a great hand
and the other times you don't.
Living in your dad's
car, always on the move,
you played the hand you
had and it paid off.
- [Announcer] Over the
shoulder and scores!
- The card's about to be dealt again Josh.
This is your time my dog.
- [Narrator] United Shades
of America with W. Kamau Bell
returns Sunday at 10 on CNN.
(audience applauds)
- And welcome to CNN's special
Democratic presidential town hall event.
We are live on the campus
of Saint Anselm College
in Manchester New Hampshire.
And right now we are talking
with California Senator Kamala Harris.
- Good to be with you Don.
- It's good to have you here.
I wanna bring in now Vanessa
Chambers she is a freshman
at Harvard studying computer science.
She is from New Orleans.
- [Kamala] Oh great.
- Hello Senator Harris how are you?
- How are you doing?
I was just in New Orleans actually.
- Oh wow! (laughs)
So my question talks
about how this country
plans to administer reparations
to the descendant of former slaves.
It's been discussed heavily,
Georgetown just voted to devote
a portion their students' tuition
to administer reparations
to the descendants
of the 272 slaves
who were sold in the 19th
century to save the school.
However this is but a small step.
What actions, what specific
actions do you plan to take
to administer reparations
for this unpaid labor.
- Right, so I'm actually
supporting a bill.
There's a congresswoman by
the name of Sheila Jackson Lee
that has written this
Bill out of the House.
Which I'm supporting to study
exactly which should be the
response to your question.
But to your point and
to support your point.
Look, we had centuries of
slavery in this country.
We had decades of Jim Crow.
We had legalized
discrimination and segregation
and then we had defacto
discrimination and segregation.
And to believe or suggest
that those years of treatment
and abuse and violence and crimes
did not have an impact is to
overlook the facts of history.
And for that reason I
support the legislation
and what we need to do
to think about specifically what it means
in terms of the next steps.
But I thank you for that question.
- Senator yes or no do you
support financial reparations?
- I support that we study them.
We should study and see
but look let's look at this for example.
One of the issues that is
very clear is that trauma,
years of trauma or even
one experience with trauma,
can lead to lifelong consequences.
I'm supporting some work
and was part of some work
that had started years ago
of looking at children who
are growing up in a community
where there is violence.
And if you look at the associated then
physical health effects
that are associated
with exposure to trauma.
And what that can mean in
terms of physical disability
not to mention what it
means in terms of a child's
ability to learn and be educated.
There are real factors that
can be associated with trauma.
And were you were talking
about the years and years
and years of trauma that were experienced
because of slavery because of Jim Crow.
And because of all that
we have seen in terms of
institutional and legal
discrimination and racism.
This is very real and it needs to studied
and we need to look at
exactly how the response
should be played out and
how it should be worked.
- I don't need to tell you
that a big voting block
in the Democratic Party, black Americans.
- Yes.
- What's your agenda for black America?
- Well it's a number of things
first of all we need to deal
with the economic status
of African Americans
in this country.
When you look at it in terms of everything
from home ownership to wages
we can see huge disparities.
And so that needs to be addressed.
Let's look at an issue
like maternal mortality.
I am actually presenting what I believe
should be the response to that.
I have studied this issue.
Black women are three to
four times more likely to die
in connection with child birth.
And when you study the
issue it becomes very clear
that it is regardless of
the socio economic status
of those women.
It is regardless of
their educational level.
It is as it turns out without
much more investigation
a matter of racial bias in the
health care delivery system.
Those women are not taken as
seriously when they show up
at the clinic or the doctor's
office or the hospital.
I am looking at it in terms
of being a proud member
and graduate of an
HBCU, Howard University.
And what we need to do
to support our HBCUs.
I was proud that we actually,
I had a piece of legislation
that actually has been passed.
To invest federal resources
and supporting our HBCUs
recognizing that HBCUs really
produce in some professions,
the majority of African Americans
who enter those professions.
So there are a number of
issues and including of course
what we need to do to reform
the criminal justice system.
- Okay, this is a, I've
done a number of town halls.
This is a fascinating question
I think that you'll find.
It's coming from Diana Ding
she's a junior at Harvard
studying computer science
from San Francisco, Diana.
- Hi Senator, thank you
for taking my question.
- Thank you.
- You have told The Root that you support
legalizing sex work.
How will you ensure that sex
workers are doing this work
because they want to and
not because they have
no opportunity to do other work?
Given that sex workers
often come from marginalized communities.
- No that's right, so what I don't support
is criminalizing these women.
So my background as you
know is I was a prosecutor.
When I was district
attorney of San Francisco
I instituted a number of policies
that were focused on women and children
and how they were
treated frankly with bias
in the criminal justice system.
Where they were criminalized
without really looking
at the real offender
and so and often that case
was the pimps and the johns.
But instead the women were
being arrested as prostitutes.
And so I created policies
that were about saying
that we really need to
focus on the other folks
and not just on the women.
I was responsible for an
initiative in San Francisco
that was about recognizing
that girls who are being trafficked
were being called teenage prostitutes.
When in fact they were the victims
of an incredible amount of
abuse and had been trafficked.
And so I created a whole
policy in San Francisco
that was one intended
to stop calling them teenage prostitutes.
But instead to call them
sexually exploited youth
and because of the work that we did,
we then created a safe
house for these young women.
So then instead of them being arrested
and put in juvenile hall they
would be in a safe house.
And then we were responsible
for actually getting legislation passed
that said that when those
johns and pimps are prosecuted
they should be prosecuted in connection
with the sale of a child.
Again looking at what need to do
to figure out who's doing what.
As it relates to women
who are being trafficked
I was one of the leaders in
the country with many others
in saying that Backpage needed
to be put out of business.
Because they were in the
business of basically allowing
the trafficking in particular
of underaged girls.
So this something that I have
had a lifelong experience with
including what we need to
go after those who traffic
girls and women and boys.
We should also be clear about that.
And I take it very seriously
but we should not be
criminalizing women who are engaged
in consensual opportunities
for employment.
But we should definitely
be careful and be sure
that they are not being
trafficked or abused in any way.
(audience applauds)
- Our next question Senator
comes from Margaret McSherry.
Margaret is a junior at Saint
Anselm College right here
studying polices and she's originally
from Massachusetts, Margaret.
- Hello Senator, a question for you.
As tensions grow between the United States
and nations like Russia and North Korea,
what should be done to prepare the nation
for the possibility of cyber warfare?
- Oh that's a great question Margaret
I'm so glad you asked it.
'Cause it's really, it's been changeling.
I've been talking about it
in the United States Senate.
I serve on the Senate
Homeland Security Committee.
Intelligence Committee.
You know newsflash Russia
interfered in the election
of the president of The United States.
(audience applauds)
And in fact on that point
about cyber security.
One, it is real.
When we talk about national
security to your point
a new form of war.
We should understand will be
cyber attacks and cyber attacks
can take a number of forms.
But usually to our
critical infrastructure.
So we've already seen one,
'cause you know what, under
the previous administration
our election system was designated
as critical infrastructure, right.
So we already know that
we have been have attacked
in terms of our elections.
We should also understand
that we are vulnerable
in terms of our electrical grids.
We are vulnerable in terms
of all of the systems
that hold together our financial systems.
That hold together our
medical care systems
and we have got to pay greater attention.
I have a bill that is a bi-partisan bill.
That is designed to strengthen
states' election systems
to prevent the next attack,
it's a bipartisan bill.
And the leader in the United States Senate
will not put in on the floor for a vote.
And this will be to our
collective peril when people
play politics with an issue
that is truly about our
vulnerability as a country.
I worked on this issue when
I was attorney general.
I was attorney general of
California for two terms.
And a lot of work that we did
there was about making sure
that we were focused on the
vulnerabilities that we have
because of technology and doing
what we can to protect it.
As the president of the
United States I will tell you
that will be one of my number one issues.
Because as far as I think
about it we're used to
and we prepare for war,
because we should and we should make sure
that we're ready in the event of.
Well this will be a war without blood
and we are not prepared and we must be.
But we cannot be in denial
and this president of the United States
is in utter denial about the realities.
- From the vulnerabilities
of our cyber system
to the vulnerabilities now of children.
Something I know that is important to you.
I wanna bring in Nicole Senders.
She's a student at Harvard
Graduate School of Education,
originally from Oregon and is a supporter
of Mayor Pete Buttigieg, Nicole.
- Hi Nicole (laughs).
- Thank you for being here tonight.
You recently mentioned your regret
of the California Truancy
Law that arrested parents
for frequently absent children.
Are there any other laws
or policies that you regret
as a prosecutor and what
actions if any would you take
to remedy this as president.
- So let me be clear, I absolutely believe
that children have and
should be thought of
to have a constitutional
right to an education.
And, period, so the truancy initiative
that you're referring to was
started by me when I was DA.
Because I took a look at who
the homicide victims were
who are under the age of 25.
People were just used to
these young men being killed
and I said wait a minute
instead of just responding
when they are killed with putting
more police on the streets
or having gang enforcement strategies.
Why aren't we asking the
question, who are they?
So I asked that question
who are these young men
who are under the age of 25
when they are being killed?
And I quickly learned that 94% of them
were high school dropouts.
I then looked closer into the issue
and learned of the chronically
and habitually truant students.
Up to 40% of them were
elementary school students
missing 50, 60 up to 80
days of 180 day school year.
So I decided to take the
issue on and I took the issue
on for a number of reasons.
One, understanding an
elementary school truant
is three to four times likely
to be a high school dropout.
70% of the prisoners in the United States
are high school dropouts.
An African American man who
was high school dropout between
the age of 20 and 24 is two
thirds likely to be in jail
have been in jail or dead.
So I took the issue on and I
said what we have got to do
is pay attention to the
fact that these children
aren't in school
and put all the resources
necessary to get them in school.
And give their parent the resources,
hold the school districts accountable.
Why aren't the school
districts raising the alarm
and putting all the resources possible
and to getting these
kids to school everyday.
And as a result of our initiative,
first of all nobody went to jail.
And as a result of our
initiative we improved attendance
by over 30% and to put
a fine point on this.
When we look at the issue of
education in our children.
No child should be overlooked
and this is what the system does guys.
For certain kids the system
really doesn't expect much
from them, that is a harsh
reality in many places.
And so when they're not
showing up in school
the system is just keeps moving.
And I said this is wrong,
let's put a spotlight on this issue.
And let's deal with it
because these children
have a capacity equal to any child
in any other school district.
And you can best believe the community
where I was talking about.
A large part of those
communities had an annual income,
household income of about $15,000.
You think if the children
in those school districts
that had a annual income
of 150 or $300,000.
You think the alarms
would not have been raised
if those children hadn't been
attending school everyday.
Much less missing up to 80
days of 180 day school year.
That's why I took that issue on.
(audience applauds)
- Another issue that I
wanna talk to you about
which is really important.
I'm not sure if you were watching earlier
but Senator Bernie Sanders
said that he in favor of felons
being able to vote
while serving in prison.
He was asked specifically about people
like the Boston Marathon bomber.
Also people who were
convicted of sexual assault
and he said this is a quote.
"The right vote is
inherent to our democracy,
"yes, even for terrible people."
Do you agree with that Senator?
- I agree that the right to vote
is one of the very important
components of citizenship.
And it is something that people
should not be stripped needlessly.
Which is why I have been long an advocate
of making sure that the
formerly incarcerated
are not denied a right to vote.
Which is the case in so
many states in our country.
In some states, permanently
deprived of the right to vote
and these are policies
that go back to Jim Crow.
These are policies that go
back to the heart of policies
that have been about disenfranchisement.
Policies that continue until today
and we need to take it seriously.
- But the people who are
convicted, in prison,
like the Boston Marathon
bomber on death row.
People who are convicted of sexual assault
they should be able to vote?
- I think we should
have that conversation.
- Okay, all right, thank you.
We're gonna have more
with Senator Kamala Harris
from the special Democratic,
this special CNN Democratic
presidential town hall event
right here after this break.
Don't go anywhere.
(audience applauds)
- Who knew.
- Yeah, so you're with the UPS store.
- Yes, in fact we
printed these right here.
- Oh I thought you guys just did shipping.
- No we do printing, packing,
faxing, notarizing, shredding,
mail-boxing, copying, taping, binding.
- Uh huh.
- Consulting, designing,
returning, storing, creating
oh and of course shipping.
- So you're into shipping?
- We also do printing, packing, faxing.
- [Narrator] Come into the
UPS store today for every ing
your small business need
and of course shipping.
- Lela, I'm in trouble please help me.
- She's till alive we've got to go.
(dramatic music)
- I'm the only person who
knows what you are doing.
- We're not always the good guy.
I just never considered myself that bad.
- They'll come after us.
- We need to get out of here.
- If I go down you go down.
- I'm taking care of it.
- It's over.
- Not for me.
- [Narrator] Deep State
returns Sunday only on Epix.
Get the channel or get the app.
- Did you know that four
out of five home owners draw
a blank when asked what their
home projects should cost.
That's why home advisor
created a national database
of home project costs.
So you can easily see what
others paid for similar projects
in your area.
Then you can get matched
with top rated pros
and read their reviews all for free.
Start your next home project
knowing what you should pay.
Go to homeadvisor.com or
download the free app.
♪ Home Advisor ♪
(doorbell rings)
- At Safelite AutoGlass we
really pride ourselves on
making it easy to get
your windshield fixed.
- Let's turn in your science papers.
- [Pascal] This teacher always
puts her students first.
- I did mine on volcanoes.
- You did, oh I can't wait to read it.
- [Pascal] So when she
had auto glass damage
she chose Safelite.
With Safelite she could see
exactly when we'd be there.
- You must be Pascal.
- Yes Ma'am.
Saving her time.
- Bye.
- [Pascal] So she can
save the science project.
♪ Safelite repairs, Safelite replace ♪
- Uh oh, looks like
someone's still nervous
about buying a new house.
- Is it that obvious?
- Yes it is.
You know maybe you'd worry
less if you got Geico to help
with your homeowner's insurance.
- I didn't know Geico helps
with homeowners insurance.
- Yeah they've been doing it for years.
What are you doing, Big Steve?
- Thanks man.
- There he is.
- [Narrator] Get to know Geico
and see how much you can save
on homeowners and renters insurance.
- We like to imagine that
after there's been a verdict
that the story is over.
(guitar music)
The reality is the
journey is just beginning.
♪ Save me ♪
- I had a lot of root canals, extractions,
always in dental pain.
I knew dentures would not be right for me
because I'm too active.
- Had a lot of cavities, root canals
eating anything cold it would hurt so bad.
- I was embarrassed of my teeth.
I don't think dentures
were ever a solution.
The only option for me was ClearChoice.
- [Narrator] The ClearChoice
one day approach is making
dental implants a reality for
people all over the country,
who suffer from missing or failing teeth.
- Because we have the surgeon
and the prosthodontist
and the lab in one facility
working together as a team,
we can perform this procedure in one day.
- They put these beautiful
teeth in my mouth
and I can eat ice cream, I can eat steak.
- [Narrator] Schedule your
free consultation today,
we'll even talk about financing options.
- I went to ClearChoice for new teeth
and I got so much more,
they changed my life.
- I get at least five or six
complements a day at work
they'll go wow those
teeth they're gorgeous.
All because of ClearChoice.
- [Narrator] Call ClearChoice today.
- I'm Chris Cuomo let's get after it.
- [Narrator] Cuomo Prime Time
tomorrow night nine eastern.
(audience applauds)
- Welcome back we are
live in New Hampshire for
a CNN special Democratic
presidential town hall.
And we wanna thank Senator
Kamala Harris for being here.
So let's jump right into the questions.
So let's bring in Sahil Lauji.
Sahil is a sophomore at
Harvard from Atlanta who says
he is supporting Senator
Bernie Sanders, Sahil.
- Hi Senator.
- Hi Sahil.
- As a fellow mixed person of
African and Indian descent,
how does our identity
serve you as president of this country?
- That's a great question.
Well you know there is something
that I feel very strongly
about this moment in time.
I think of this as being
an inflection point
in the history of our country.
I think this is a moment in
time for a variety of reasons.
That is requiring us
all to look in mirror,
each one of us and collectively,
look in a mirror, and ask a question.
That question being who are we.
And I believe part of the
answer to that question
is we are better than this.
The other part of it is understanding that
in this inflection moment
there are very powerful voices
in our country right now
that are trying to sow
hate and division among us.
And we need to speak many
truths and one of them is this.
The vast majority of us
have so much more in common
than what separates us and
I know that to be true.
I know it to be true
because I have been exposed
to many cultures, right, you got me.
(audience laughs)
Right there you go so I
know it to be true based on
what I call the middle
of the night thought.
Some people call it three
in the morning thought
other people call it the witching hour.
You know what I'm talking about.
When you wake up in
the middle of the night
with that thought that's
been weighing on you.
For the vast majority of us
when we wake up in the middle
of the night thinking that thought.
It is never through the lens of the party
with which we're registered to vote.
For the vast majority
of us when we wake up
thinking that thought,
it is never through the
lens of some simplistic
demographic a pollster put us in.
And for the vast majority
of us when we wake up
thinking that thought it
usually has to do with
one of just a very few things.
Our personal health, the
health of our children,
or our parents.
For so many Americans can
I get a job, keep a job,
pay the bills by the end of
the month, retire with dignity.
For our students can I pay
off those student loans.
For so many family members in America
can I help my family member
get off their opioid addiction?
The vast majority of us
have so much more in common
than what separates us.
And while there are these
powerful forces that are trying
to sow hate and division
among us and have us pointing
fingers at each other and
oh you're that and I'm this.
I say I'm not buying it, I'm not buying it
and that's how I think
about my experiences.
I know how much we have in
common and right now our country
requires leaders and the top leader,
to, instead of using a microphone in way
that is about fueling the fan of hate,
instead of using the bully pulpit
of the president of the
United States in a way
that is about talking about
well on both sides there is merit.
We need leadership in this
country who has through personal
experience and through
ideals and through just
an ability to see who
people are and speak truth.
We need leadership that
understands the vast majority of us
have so much more in common
than what separates us.
And they've gotta stop diving us
and that's why I'm running for president,
that's one of the reasons.
- Let's talk about--
(audience applauds)
Let's talk about the vision
and I think this falls into that category.
Because you have said,
recently said, that it would be
a trap, it would be a mistake
for democrats to fall into
a trap of a conversation
about winning back quote.
"The guy in the Midwest
which is code" unquote.
What is it code for what
do you mean by that?
- What I mean is that there is
a conversation that has been
happening among many
people including pundits.
That suggest, no I don't mean you.
(laughs)
- I didn't think so but thank
you, thanks for clarifying.
- I just meant on TV.
(laughs)
I just keep digging myself into this.
They will be talking of
course about my performance
tonight those same pundits.
Okay in any event, there is
a conversation that all of us
have been hearing about,
especially the 2020 election.
Which is a conversation saying
oh who can talk to the
person in the Midwest.
And I just reject that notion
that you have one conversation
with someone in the Midwest.
And another conversation
with somebody in the South.
And another conversation with
people who live on the coast.
I reject that notion and I
think it is short sighted
and it is actually not connected
with where people really are.
The American public don't want that.
(audience applauds)
They don't want that.
So that's what I meant by that comment.
- All right, let's bring
in now Kimberly Morrow.
She is a senior studying
politics and has worked full time
while attending school
at the University of New
Hampshire Manchester.
Kimberly what's your question?
- Good evening Senator.
Through my studies as a
polices and society major
at UNH Manchester, I've learned
that women in our country face
very real inequalities in the workplace.
Women trail men in income,
promotion to leadership positions
and labor force participation rates.
What do you plan to do as president
to level the playing field
and empower working women?
- Well on day one we need to pass the ERA,
Equal Rights Amendment.
We also need to speak
louder about the realities
of the facts just as you've done now
and thank you for your leadership on this.
Because it is something
that has to be acknowledged
and dealt with.
Women are paid on
average 70% to the dollar
and then if you look at African
American women and Latinas
even less and for doing the same work.
You look at the fact that
we have a real battle
in this country around minimum wage
and the need to increase minimum wage.
We should understand minimum
wage is a minimum standard
of living but federal minimum
wage is $7.25 an hour,
which averages $15,000 a year
and the majority of women
are minimum wage workers.
Let's look at the issue of
what we need to do around
disparities around issues like childcare.
Understanding that women
are the primary caregiver
to children and yet we
don't have a national policy
around affordable childcare
which I'm a proponent of.
We need to also address what
is happening in terms of
understanding that women's
issues to the point of being
marginalized have to
brought to the forefront.
And we should also reject the conversation
that women's issues are just for women
to be concerned about.
When in fact the reality
is that when you lift up
the economic status of women.
You lift up the economic
status of families
and communities and all of society.
That's how I feel about that.
(audience applauds)
- Matthew Solomon is from
Massachusetts he's a junior at
Saint Anselm studying politics
and peace and justice.
He's also the president of the school's
LGBTQ alliance, Matthew.
- Hi Senator thanks for being here.
- Of course.
- So my question is if elected president
what kind of protections,
specific protections,
will you providing for
the LBGTQ plus community
and especially those who lack visibility
and safety like the transgender community
and LBGTQ plus community members of color.
- Right, so I have my entire career
and life been an ally of LBGTQ community
and I will say that we must have a country
that agrees that no
group should be treated
without equality under the law.
And right now that is the case
and we have got to change it.
I am on day one would pass
the Equality Act to make sure
that we actually correct
what is wrong and give LBGTQ
people equal rights under the law.
This is a civil rights
and human rights issue
and we must address it.
And I'll tell you my background on this.
I was as attorney general, it
was one of the pivotal issues
in my race to become attorney general.
Whether or not the elected
attorney general would defend
a patently unconstitutional law
which denied same sex
couples the right to marry.
I said I would not defend it
because I knew it to be unconstitutional.
I won and I did not
defend it, prop eight went
to the United States Supreme Court.
We won and the wedding bells
rang across the country.
I'm very proud of that, I
will tell you back in 2004.
When the chatter among a lot of Democrats
was about civil unions, I
was marrying same sex couples
at San Francisco City Hall.
(audience applauds)
I will tell you.
You'll remember the tragic cases
involving transgender men who were killed.
And there was this defense
that was happening in Court.
Where the murderer was calling
it the gay panic defense.
Oh, I panicked cause I didn't
know he was gay and therefore
I should not be convicted of
murder and this was happening
around the Matthew Shepherd
case, around that era.
When I was district
attorney of San Francisco
knowing this was happening.
I brought DAs from around
the country to San Francisco
where I hosted and created
a training for prosecutors
around the country on how to
defeat the gay panic defense.
On the issue of transgender rights.
Listen right now in
particular we have a president
who is reviving, you
know the courts said no,
but then that changed.
And now we've got a president who is
basically putting in place a process
for discharging transgender men and women
who have made a commitment to our country
and to defend our democracy
at great service and potential sacrifice.
And this president wants to
kick them out of the military
because they are transgender.
It is absolutely unconscionable
and that is something
I would reverse immediately
when I am elected president
of the United States.
(audience applauds)
- I wanna bring in Rachel Damle.
Rachel is a sophomore at Harvard
she's from Colorado, Rachel.
- Hi Senator.
- Hi Rachel.
- The past couple of years
have seen young people getting
involved in politics and activism.
Organizing around issues
such as gun control
and climate change.
Given that policies passed
now will affect the younger
generation for years to come.
Do you believe that Americans should have
the right to vote at age 16?
- I'm really interested in
having that conversation
I have to tell you that.
I think that there is no question
that if we are looking at
what is going on in our country.
We are putting more responsibilities
on people at a younger age.
And the larger number of
people that we can involve
in the electoral process,
I think the more robust it will be.
I think one of the downsides
of the way that our system
is currently constructed.
But thanks to CNN for doing
this town hall with students,
is that if people don't vote
or they don't write checks
they don't get heard.
And I believe strongly that
you can judge a society
based on how it treats its children.
And you can look at what we
are not doing for our students
for our teenagers and even younger.
And I believe that if they
had greater political power
maybe we would get our act together
a little bit better than
what we've been doing
and maybe that's one
of the steps toward it.
I will also say though that
what I am so excited about
in terms of seeing who's
here and I know you guys have
been here for like five hours.
(laughs)
- They have.
- Is that one of things
that we have to remember
about the history of our country
is some of the greatest movements
that we have had that
have brought about change,
social change, advancement, progress
have been fueled and
born from our students.
- Thank you senator.
- Thank you.
- That's it for Senator.
Thank you, I know it went by fast right?
So we wanna thank Senator Kamala Harris
we wish you all the very best.
That is four town halls
down tonight one more to go
and when we come back Anderson
Cooper's gonna be here
with South Bend Indiana Mayor
Pete Buttigieg for our final
CNN Democratic presidential
town hall of the night.
(audience applauds)
- [Narrator] The right gear matters.
Introducing the all new 2019 Ford Ranger.
It's the right gear.
With a terrain management system for this.
A bash plate for that,
and electronic locking rear
differential for yeah this.
Heading to the supermarket get any truck.
Heading out here, get the Ford Ranger.
The only adventure gear built Ford tough.
(upbeat drum music)
- [Narrator] Every day visionaries
are creating the future.
So everyday we put our latest technology
and unrivaled network to work.
The United States Postal
Service makes more eCommerce
deliveries to homes than
anyone else in the country.
Because the future only
happens with people
who really know how to deliver it.
♪ Just grilling and chilling ♪
♪ My favorite kind of time killing ♪
♪ No running, no sunning ♪
- [Narrator] Applebee's
bigger bolder grill combos
now that's eating good
in the neighborhood.
- [Man] Welcome to Sun
Spring's retirement community.
- What brings you here?
- Oh I'm just here to die.
- Uh huh.
- [Narrator] When you've
got nothing to lose.
- You were a cheerleader.
- My mother was sick so I quit the team.
- Maybe you should give it another shot.
- [Narrator] Nothing can stop you.
- We wanna start a cheerleading club.
- Nobody wants to see that.
- Maybe he should take his opinions
and shove 'em up his--
- Hey!
- You know what.
- [Narrator] On May 10th,
being bold never gets old.
- Life's short, in the meantime
you should be dancing your ass off.
- [Narrator] Poms, rated PG-13.
(dramatic piano music)
- [Woman] You got this!
- Woo!
- [Narrator] This is an
apple, and this is an apple,
and this is an apple and when
you put them all together
you've got a case.
(soft piano music)
- Yeah we're gonna need
500 more units pronto.
- We don't have that kind
of money right now Carl.
- You will in 10 minutes
that's how long it will take
you to get funding through Kabbage.
I know, I'm 10 minutes
in the future spokesguy.
- What's happening?
- And I'm 10 days in the future spokesguy.
That Kabbage funding helped you win
the Gundelfinger account, congratulations.
- What's a Gundelfinger?
- And I'm from 10 years in the future.
- [Narrator] Kabbage, business funding
in as little as 10 minutes.
- What did I miss?
- [Salesman] I bet you've
never seen a bed like this.
It's the new Craftmatic Legacy
Rising Pillow Rest Adjustable Bed.
Featuring bed-side power
plugs under-bed night lights
and more for less.
Up to 50% less than
Tempur-Pedic, Sleep Number
and other adjustables.
Call now, you gotta see
how little they cost.
- [Speaker] Congratulations
you're a writer.
But wait you have to
actually publish your book.
Discover Publishers will help
you find the right publisher
to get your book in book stores.
It's completely free.
- [Narrator] Go to freeauthorinfo.com
or call us at 800-251-4119.