- [Announcer] But it's
not, this is an apple.
(soft music)
- Have you been told you can't get
high speed internet where you live?
Well you can with Hughes Net Gen5.
Experience the power of next generation
satellite internet wherever you live.
Hughes Net Gen5 is
fast, you'll get 25 Mbps
plus built-in wi-fi and
there's no hard data limits.
So wherever you live now you can do
more of everything you love online.
Connect on social media.
Stay informed.
Watch the latest videos.
And help your kids get ahead.
No wonder Hughes Net is America's
number one choice for satellite internet.
- [Announcer] Act now to save big
with our limited time offer.
Get free standard installation
by calling right now.
- So what are you waiting for?
Get Hughes Net Gen5.
- [Announcer] To order
call 1-800-748-5218.
Be sure to ask about our
home phone service too.
Call 1-800-748-5218 today.
- [Announcer] The Situation
Room with Wolf Blitzer,
tomorrow at 5:00 eastern on CNN.
(dramatic music)
- And welcome back to
this very special night at
St. Anselm College in
Manchester, New Hampshire.
I'm Anderson Cooper.
We are just getting started with our
CNN Democratic presidential
town hall event.
In the last hour, you heard
from Senator Amy Klobuchar.
And later tonight, you'll
see town halls with
Senators Bernie Sanders and Kamala Harris,
and Mayor Pete Buttigieg.
Right now, Senator Elizabeth
Warren of Massachusetts.
Now, to pull this event off tonight,
CNN has partnered with
Harvard University's
Institute of Politics,
which has just released
its youth poll examining
the political opinions of young Americans.
And also with the New
Hampshire Institute of Politics
right here at Saint Anselm College.
Throughout, the night the
candidates will take questions
from these young college
students and young adults who are
in the auditorium who
say they plan to vote in
their state's Democratic
primaries and caucuses.
So, please welcome to the
stage, Senator Elizabeth Warren.
(audience applauds and cheers)
Welcome.
- Hi, it's good to see you.
(audience applauds and cheers)
- Hi.
All right.
- You want to have a seat?
- Are we going to do students?
- Let's go right to it.
- In that case, I want closer.
Have to keep an eye on the
ones in the back, oaky.
- I want to start with
your big announcement today
about college affordability.
Obviously, it could impact
a lot of students here.
For that, I want to bring in
Dena Miller from Massachusetts.
She's a junior at St. Anselm
College studying history, Dena.
- Hi, Dena.
- Hi, Senator.
I like so many other students
had to take out loans
to pay for my education that I
will be paying off for years.
What is your plan to
deal with student debt
and the rising cost of education?
- Okay, thanks for the question, Dena.
You know, this is the
America we live in now.
Basically to get a shot
at a middle class life,
you've got to have some post
high school technical training,
two-year college, four-year
college, maybe graduate school,
depending on who you are and
what you're ending up doing.
The position of the federal
government has been,
good luck to you, you're on your own.
The one thing they've done
is they've lent tens of
thousands, hundreds of
thousands, millions,
billions of dollars to our students.
And it is now crushing them.
So, my proposal is to
say, this isn't right.
What we have to do as a
country is roll back that debt.
And so, I have two parts to the proposal.
Part one is that we say that
we're going to roll back
student loan debt for about
95% of students who have debt.
That's part one.
And part two is to make sure
that we never get in this mess
again on student loan debt
and that is to make college
universally available with
free tuition and fees,
and to put more money into Pell grants
so that students of color,
so that our poorest students
have real access to college
and that we put real money
into our historically black
colleges and universities.
This is about opportunity for everyone.
(audience applauds)
And can we talk about how to pay for it?
- I was just about to ask for it.
- Just for a minute, you want to ask?
- Well, that is the criticism
obviously from Republicans
who say how you're going to
pay for it, and even from
centrist Democrats who say
doesn't this feed the narrative
that Democrats want to give
everything away for free.
- So, let's remember
where this all started.
I started several months
ago about a wealth tax,
an ultra millionaire's tax.
It's 2 cents on every dollar of
the great fortunes above $50 million.
So, your 50 millionth and
first dollar, you've got to pay
2 cents and 2 cents on all
of the dollars after that.
And here's the stunning part.
If we ask the great fortunes
in this country, understand,
this isn't about trying to be nasty
or say you've done anything wrong,
what it's about is saying,
look, you had a great idea.
You got out there.
You worked hard or you inherited
well, whichever one it was.
(audience applauds and cheers)
But now that you've
got that great fortune,
spend just a minute to
remember how you got it.
You built that great business
or your ancestors did
using workers that all of
us helped pay to educate.
You got your goods to market using roads
and bridges that all of
us helped pay to build.
You are protected in your
factories with firefighters
and police officers that
all of us helped to pay.
And we say, good for you,
that you have now gotten this
great fortune, but 2 cents.
You've got to pay something back
so everybody else gets a chance.
And here's how the money works out.
If we put that 2 cent
wealth tax in place on the
75,000 largest fortunes
in this country, 2 cents,
we can do universal child care
for every baby zero to five,
universal pre-K, universal
college and knock back the
student loan debt burden
for 95% of our students
and still have nearly a
trillion dollars left over.
(audience applauds and cheers)
Yeah.
- I want you to,
this is actually kind of related.
I want you to meet Meghan
McCormick from Pennsylvania.
- Hi, Meghan.
- She's a graduate, you
got to listen to this,
she's a graduate student
at Harvard and MIT.
She's also a contributor
at Forbes, where she covers
women running high impact
organizations in Africa.
You make me feel like a shlub, I mean.
(audience laughs)
- What do you do in
your spare time, Meghan?
It's good to see you.
- Thank you for being here.
So, Amazon's monopoly means that I
can buy generic goods and brand names from
my phone and receive them on my doorstep
without a delivery fee within 24 hours.
How is breaking up big tech good for me?
- Okay, good question, Meghan.
So, here's what we want
to remember about Amazon,
about Google, about Apple,
about a lot of these giant tech companies.
They actually run two businesses.
So, one is the platform.
That's the place where people
come to buy and sell goods.
That's where you go to get
whatever it is, you know,
you can compare 48 printers
and get it all delivered
in less than 24 hours.
Got it.
Cool.
That's the platform.
Just so you get an idea of
the scale here for Amazon,
Walmart does about 9% of
all retail sales in America.
If you want to sell online,
Amazon is doing about 49%
of all retail sales that
are happening in America.
So that is the marketplace.
So, Amazon runs the marketplace.
I'm cool with that.
I'm all for a marketplace.
But Amazon does a second
thing and that is they collect
information on every buyer
and seller who comes through.
Every time you go to buy something,
they get your information
and they aggregate it
with the other information
they had about you.
Every time you come to sell
something, they get information.
And then they see that,
whoa, over there it looks
like pet pillows is starting
to make a big profit.
Huh, says Amazon.
I know what let's do.
Let's jump in front of pet
pillows and do Amazon pet pillows
and move pet pillows from the
front page back to page 16.
And the consequence is that Amazon,
because of its superior information,
can come in and knock out
all of the competition.
Now this is a real thing,
Meghan, that's happening.
And here's what we know
as a consequence of this,
is that the area around
these giants are referred to
by venture capitalists,
investors, as the dead zone
because it means you try
to start up a business,
you just run the risk that
Amazon steps in front of you
or Google steps in front of you
or they buy you out before you
have a chance to get started.
Look, here's how I see it.
You can run the platform,
that is, you can be the umpire
in the baseball game and you
can run an honest platform,
or you can be a player, that
is, you can have a business
or you can have a team in the
game, but you don't get to
be the umpire and have a team in the game.
If we break off the
platform from the parts
that are competing, what
you'll see in America
is a platform that works really well.
It's a very profitable business,
but you'll see a lot more
competition where little businesses have a
chance to get going, where
when you've got a good idea
you can build that good
idea into something,
where there's really a chance for
everybody to get in and compete.
So that's the reason I want to see
the two of them broken apart.
- Do you order stuff from Amazon?
- Sure.
- You do?
What was the last thing
you ordered, do you know?
- A mailbox.
(audience laughs)
- Okay.
(audience applauds)
What did they put the mailbox
in when they deliver it?
- It comes in a box.
It was a box of mailbox.
- We have another question now.
This is Seth Filo from Arizona.
He's a freshman at Harvard, a
supporter of Mayor Buttigieg.
Seth?
- Senator Warren, in 2012,
you opposed the legalization
of marijuana nationwide.
And then in 2013, as
senator of Massachusetts,
you oppose the state
initiative for legalization.
Yet in 2016, you came out in support
of the legalization of
marijuana nationwide.
What are your honest views on the
legalization of marijuana
and marijuana legislation?
And if they have, why have they changed?
- So, actually, I supported Massachusetts
changing its laws on marijuana.
Massachusetts had
decriminalized at that point
and I thought it made a lot
more sense for Massachusetts
to go ahead and legalize marijuana,
and I now support the
legalization of marijuana.
And let me tell you at least
a couple of reasons why.
The first one is, it's just
a plain old science reason.
It makes no darn sense
that right now in America,
we treat marijuana as a schedule 1 drug,
which means in effect
the federal government
has determined in advance
that it has no medicinal use,
that it can't have any good effects,
no research is supposed to be done.
It makes it very hard
to do research on it.
And that's just, we should
be doing this, right?
We should be looking into it.
But the second reason is
because of the racial impact
of the enforcement of marijuana laws.
You know, right now in this country,
the best evidence suggests
that African-Americans
and whites use marijuana
at about the same rates,
and yet African-Americans
are far more likely to be
arrested for marijuana
use than whites are.
So, every time we start to talk about
criminal justice reform, for
example, I think a good place
to start is with the things we
make illegal, and one of the
best places we could start
is by legalizing marijuana.
- I want you to meet Jackson
Dwyer, he's from Massachusetts.
He's a senior at St. Anselm College.
Jackson?
- Hi, Jackson.
- Hi, Senator.
You have often been a
vocal critic of police
and the criminal justice system,
both the state and the federal levels.
As a young Massachusetts voter
and aspiring police officer
who's lived through countless tragedies,
including the recent murders
of Sergeant Gannon of Yarmouth
and Officer Michael Chesna of Weymouth,
how can you assure me
that you will support
legislation that keeps
law enforcement safe?
- So that's a very good question.
I appreciate your asking it.
You know, I talk with a lot of
people in different parts of
the criminal justice system,
people who are in law enforcement,
people who are in the judicial system,
people when they are incarcerated,
various parts of it, and what all of them
tell me is we've got a problem.
Our criminal justice system is broken.
And right at the heart
of that problem is race.
And we have to address this head on.
So let me just give you
some basic information about
what's happening right now in
our criminal justice system.
Study after study after
study shows us that
African-Americans compared
with whites are more
likely to be for exactly the same crimes,
they're more likely to be arrested,
they're more likely to be arraigned,
they are more likely to be taken to trial.
They are more likely to
be wrongfully convicted
and they are more likely to
receive harsher sentences.
That is a criminal justice
system that is not only
locking up too many people, it
is a criminal justice system
that has a problem of race
right at the heart of it,
and we need to call it out for what it is.
(audience applauds)
No one is safer in a world where we
have a broken criminal justice system.
So let me just go through a couple
of the parts directly to your question.
I said on the first part,
one way we can help fix this
system is take a look at
what it is we make illegal.
How about the next part
in the judicial system?
We need to make sure that
everybody is entitled
and gets good legal representation.
Throughout the system, we
want to make sure the right
people are incarcerated and
not the wrong people because
they couldn't afford to hire a lawyer.
Justice is not just
for those who are rich,
justice is for everyone,
and the only way we're
gonna get that in America
is if we're able to put
the resources into it.
Third part of this is we should get
rid of for-profit private prisons.
It is an outrage in America.
(audience applauds)
Fourth is that when people
leave the prison system,
they need to be reintegrated
into their communities.
They need to be able to
have a chance to get a job,
to be able to find decent
housing, and they need to be
able to participate in
the political process.
And that means they need the
right to vote to be reinstated.
They are American citizens.
(audience applauds)
And one more, you talk about safety for
our police officers and you are right.
This is a very serious issue.
One of the main ways that we
could help make our police
safer is to get serious about
gun safety in this country.
(audience applauds)
You mentioned Sergeant Gannon's
tragic death in Massachusetts.
I wrote an op-ed with his parents about
asking for our leaders across
this country to step up
and pass some sensible gun safety laws.
We need universal background checks.
We need to take weapons of
war off our city streets.
Right now, we live in America where
seven children and teenagers
will die every single day,
where the lives of
officers are put at risk.
We need as a country to step
up, to be more responsible,
to be willing to push back against the NRA
and to put some sensible
gun safety laws in place.
I think that will be
the best that we can do.
Thank you.
Thank you for your question.
(audience applauds and cheers)
- [Anderson] This is Ellie Taylor.
She's from Wisconsin.
She's a student at Harvard
and she's a freshman.
Ellie, welcome.
- Hi, Ellie.
- Hi, Senator.
So, this isn't as much of
a policy-based question.
But some have voiced
concerns about you getting
Hillaried in the election,
meaning that you get held
to a higher standard
than your opponent for
potentially arbitrary or
may be even sexist reasons.
So what lessons have you learned from 2016
that will help you to
kind of navigate these
situations when you
might be criticized for
something that's partially
motivated by sexist?
- So, that's a really good
question, but if I can,
I want to go back before 2016.
Can we all just let our
hair down here for a minute?
This didn't just start in 2016, right?
Been around for a while.
(audience applauds)
I'll tell you when I ran into it big time.
I never thought I was going
to be in elected politics.
I've known what I wanted
to do all my life.
I wanted to be a teacher.
And I thought that
would be my job forever.
And during the crash, I
end up down in Washington
setting up a consumer
agency for President Obama.
After I did that for a
year, the Republicans said,
we're never going to let
her stay and run that thing.
So, I came back to Massachusetts.
And there was an incumbent Republican,
a very popular Republican
incumbent who had the
Senate seat and he was
coming up for reelection.
Understand, he had high approval ratings,
he had a bucket of money in
the bank from Wall Street,
and he had just beaten a
woman who was really good
and everybody thought was going to win.
So, I start getting these
phone calls from people
and they say, Elizabeth, you should run
against him for the Senate seat.
You should do it.
Go ahead.
You should do this thing.
You're going to lose, but
you should definitely do,
these were Democrats calling me.
Saying, you should do this.
You're going to lose.
All I can say is, Democrats,
get a better message.
(audience applauds)
But people said to me,
you're going to lose because
Massachusetts in 2011,
according to conventional wisdom,
was not ready to have a
woman senator or governor.
We never had and people said
it's just not going to happen,
not at least for another generation.
Now you can imagine how I heard that.
I heard that as, get in this race,
right now, which is what I did.
So I jumped in the race and sure enough,
you know, the early coverage
is about what I'm wearing.
It's about my hair.
It's about my voice.
It's about whether or not I smile enough.
I didn't.
It was every part of that.
And this kept up and I thought, you know,
look, I'm going to be in this race.
I'm going to make something
count every single day.
So every day when I saw a little girl,
I would come up and I'd usually
get down, I'm a teacher,
and I would say, hi, my name is Elizabeth
and I'm running for Senate
because that's what girls do.
(audience applauds and cheers)
And then we would pinky swear to remember.
And so, every night when I went home,
no matter what the day had
been like, I would count up
how many pinky swears we
had done during the day.
And I kept getting out there
and hammering my message.
I kept getting out there
talking about what's happening
with working families across the country,
talking about how Washington
works great for the rich
and the powerful, just not
working for anyone else,
and how we've got to
fight back against that.
So I talked about it every
single day and ultimately,
I went from 17 points behind that
guy to beating him by seven and a half.
So, the way I see it is here
we are in a presidential,
and it's the same kind of
you stay after it every day.
One might say you persist.
(audience applauds)
Organize, build a grassroots movement,
fight for working people,
and that's how I'm going
to be the first woman
elected president of the United States.
Thank you.
- We're going to take a quick break.
We'll be right back more with
the CNN presidential town hall
live in St. Anselm College
in Manchester, New Hampshire.
Stay with us.
(audience applauds and cheers)
- [Announcer] Leave no man
behind or child or other child.
Or their new friend.
Or your giant nephews and their giant dad.
Or a horse.
Or a horse's brother for that matter.
The room for eight 9000
pound towing Ford Expedition.
(soft music)
- [Announcer] Everyone's
gotta listen to mom.
When it comes to reducing the
sugar in your family's diet
Coke, Dr Pepper and Pepsi hear you
and we're working
together to do just that.
Bringing you more great tasting
beverages with less sugar
or no sugar at all.
Smaller portion sizes.
Clear calorie labels and
reminders to think balance.
Because we know mom wants what's best.
More beverage choices,
smaller portions, less sugar.
Balanceus.org.
- [Announcer] Feel the
clarity of non drowsy Claritin
and relief form symptoms
caused by over 200
indoor and outdoor allergens,
like those from Buddy.
Because stuffed animals are clearly
no substitute for the real ones.
Feel the clarity and live Claritin clear.
- [Man] Tolkien sir, where you going?
- Up the line to find a friend.
- [Man] He must be a very good friend.
- [Tolkien] He'd do the same for me.
- We are your brothers Tolkien.
This more than just a friendship,
it's an invincible alliance.
- A fellowship.
(dramatic music)
- Tolkien!
- Geoffrey!
- [Announcer] Tolkien, rated PG 13.
In theaters everywhere May 10th.
- We bought a house in a neighborhood
with a lot of other young couples.
Then we noticed something strange.
Oh, could you make me a burger?
- [Men] Poof, you're a burger.
- Everyone acts like their parents.
- You have a tattoo.
- Yes.
- Fun, do you not work?
- So what kind of mower have you got Seth?
- I don't know, I have
some kid comes over,
we pay him to do it.
- But it's not all bad,
someone even showed us how we
can save money by bundling
home and auto with Progressive.
- [Announcer] Progressive
can't protect you from becoming
your parents but we can
protect your home and auto.
- Your mother murdered,
your daughter shot dead,
now imagine sitting in front of
the person who was responsible.
See what happens when
victims and their offenders
meet face to face.
- [Announcer] The Redemption
Projection with Van Jones,
premiers Sunday at 9:00.
- What's up Kyler it's Dak.
- [Announcer] The 135th
pick, Dak Prescott.
- [Dak] Trust me, I know
what it's like to be doubted.
- [Announcer] He's entirely too small.
- [Announcer] He shouldn't
even play quarterback.
- [Dal] Remember though, doubt is a gift.
It takes you to the next level.
- [Announcer] Kyler Murray is the
best player in college football.
- So what if they doubt you?
They doubted me too.
Go get 'em bro.
- [Matt] SO you take six
people that are about play good
friends and you throw
'em all in the same room
and it really worked out great.
- [Jennifer] Why am I getting noticed
for my haircut and not for my work?
- [David] He stuck me as a romantic.
I just thought this is a guy I can play.
- [Matthew] When it got out of control
I went in and I faced my fear.
- [Lisa] The six of us have a lot more
power than one star of the show.
- I'm Natalie Morales, join me for
Friends Behind Closed Doors,
an all new Celebrity Sunday
Special on Reelz Channel 238.
- [Announcer] United Shades
Of America with W. Kamau Bell
returns Sunday at 10:00 on CNN.
- And welcome back.
We're live in Manchester, New Hampshire,
for a special CNN Democratic
presidential town hall event.
Five town halls tonight, with some of the
top Democratic contenders, all of them are
taking questions from college students.
Right now, it is Senator
Elizabeth Warren's turn.
We're going to have questions
from the audience in a minute.
I do just want to ask you, you
have called for impeachment
proceedings to be initiated
against President Trump.
What do you say to those
Democrats who say, look,
this is not the time,
it's going to take away the
focus from winning in 2020?
Speaker Pelosi told her caucus
again just today that she
no plans to immediately initiate
impeachment proceedings.
- So, there is no political inconvenience
exception to the United
States Constitution.
(audience applauds)
This one is, if I can, I
want to take a little time
on this because I think
this is really important.
Last Thursday, I had been out,
I had been to South Carolina.
This was all about climate change.
That's where I was, South Carolina,
coastal communities that were
protesting off shore drilling.
I then came to Colorado, the
biggest drought in 1,200 years.
And then to Utah where they had one of the
worst wildfire seasons in a generation.
I'm on an airplane and
the Mueller report drops.
And so, I start reading
it on the airplane,
I read it on through the evening,
I read it into the wee
hours of the morning.
And when I get to the end,
three things just jump off the page.
I don't care if you're a
Democrat, a Republican,
an independent, a
libertarian, a vegetarian.
Three things just totally
jump off the page.
The first is that a hostile
foreign government attacked
our 2016 election in order
to help Donald Trump.
The evidence is just there.
Read it, footnote after footnote,
page after page documentation.
Part two, Donald Trump welcomed that help.
So, on the first one about what they did,
understand, this was a
sophisticated attack.
They attacked part of voting system.
That's going to be an ongoing
federal investigation.
They hacked into more than
50 computers at the DNC,
the DCCC, a very serious attack.
And Donald Trump welcoming it,
in the Mueller report, just read it.
He gets off the phone
from an unnamed caller
and looks up and says to the
other person on the phone,
there are more leaks coming.
The idea that he was welcoming
what was happening from the
Russian government, and
by the summer of 2016,
the report documents that by that point,
the Trump campaign
actually had a worked out
formal process for dealing
with the leaks that were
coming in from the Russians.
So that's part two.
Part three is when the
federal government starts
to investigate part one and part two,
Donald Trump took repeated
steps aggressively to try to
halt the investigation,
derail the investigation,
push the investigation somewhere else,
but otherwise keep that
investigation from going forward
and turning into a serious investigation
about a hostile foreign government that
attacked us and about his
own personal interests.
So, here's how I see this, if
any other human being in this
country had done what's
documented in the Mueller report,
they would be arrested and put in jail.
Obstruction of justice is a
serious crime in this country.
But Mueller believed because
of the directions from
Donald Trump's Justice Department
that he could not bring
a criminal indictment
against a sitting president.
I think he's wrong on that,
but that's what he believed.
So he serves the whole thing up to
the United States Congress
and says, in effect,
if there's going to be any accountability,
that accountability has
to come from the Congress.
And the tool that we are given for
that accountability is
the impeachment process.
This is not about politics.
This is about principle.
This is about what kind
of a democracy we have.
In a dictatorship, everything
in government revolves
around protecting the
one person at the center,
but not in our democracy and
not under our Constitution.
We have checks and balances,
and we have to proceed here
in a way understanding our
place in history that not
only protects democracy
now, but protects democracy
when the next president comes in
and the next president and
the president after that.
That's our responsibility.
(audience applauds)
- But you started off by saying,
by talking about some of your
travels and people talking
about climate change and their
concerns and tabletop issues.
- Yes.
- Doesn't putting a lot of
Democrats' focus on impeaching
the president, which is not
going to pass in the Senate,
it's not really going to
go anywhere in that sense,
doesn't that take away focus
from the tabletop issues
that you and other Democrats
say they want to run on?
- So, you know, let me just
say, if you've actually
read the Mueller report,
it's all laid out there.
It's not like it's going to take
a long time to figure this out.
It's there.
It's got the footnotes.
It's got the points.
It connects directly to the law.
But this really is fundamentally,
I took an oath to uphold the Constitution
of the United States,
and so did everybody else in
the Senate and in the House.
And I believe that every person
in the Senate and the House
ought to have to vote
and to say either, yeah,
that's okay with me, yeah,
let a president just step in
the way he did when he
told the White House
counsel to go fire Mueller,
and then told the White
House counsel to go lie about
having told the White House
counsel to go fire Mueller,
and then told the White
House counsel to write
a letter saying that Donald Trump had not
told him to go fire
Mueller, and then to say,
why on Earth would you take
notes about what I said to you?
The lawyers I deal with never
put anything in writing.
If there are people in the
House or the Senate who want to
say that's what a president
can do when the president is
being investigated for his own
wrongdoings or when a foreign
government attacks our country,
then they should have to
take that vote and live with
it for the rest of their lives.
(audience applauds)
- I want you to meet,
this is Cecilia D'Arms.
Cecilia is a sophomore at
Harvard from Columbus, Ohio,
studying social studies.
She interned for Hillary
Clinton's presidential campaign.
Cecilia?
- Hi, Cecelia.
- Hi.
You were registered as
a Republican until 1995.
- I was.
- But you've since become one of
the most progressive people in Congress.
Did you change your beliefs?
Or do you believe that the political
parties changed around you?
- So understand this, Cecilia.
I grew up in a family
that wasn't political.
I grew up out in Oklahoma,
and to this day I couldn't
tell you how my parents were registered
or my grandparents or
much of anybody else.
My mom always voted.
I know that.
And in fact, she worked
at the polls sometimes,
but we weren't a political family.
And when I was a young mom
and struggling to try to keep
up with my job and get dinner on the table
and take care of a couple of little kids
and launch my career, I didn't
think much about politics.
Now, I've been a policy
person for a long, long time,
so I think the question
you're asking me is,
when does the change come?
And that I can tell you.
So in late mid-1990s, I had
been working over and over and
over on what's happening to
America's working families,
to America's middle class,
how it is that people who work
hard, who play by the
rules are just finding the
path steeper and rockier year by year,
and for people of color even
steeper and even rockier.
This is my life's work.
And so I keep working on this about
what's changing in America.
I'm studying families that go bankrupt.
And the credit card companies,
half-dozen giant credit card
companies figure out that if
they can get the bankruptcy
laws changed, that what will
happen is they can improve
their bottom line by just a
little by keeping people
locked out of bankruptcy.
Never mind that there's people are
head over heels in medical debts,
that they've had job losses
that have put them way behind,
that they've had a death
or divorce in the family,
but they've been cheated
by credit card companies
and mortgage companies.
Never mind any of that.
Just improve the bottom line
for the credit card companies.
Man, I looked around in
the middle of that fight
and I realized all the
money was on one side
and all the hurting was on the other.
And that's when I jumped in politically.
I got in that fight, and
I fought it for 10 years.
And by the end of that fight,
I fully understood that
every single Republican stood
there for the banks and
half of the Democrats did.
So my party was the party
that at least we got half of
them to stand up for working people,
and that was the big change for me.
(audience applauds)
- This is Eric Jjemba,
a sophomore at Harvard.
You can tell from his sweatshirt.
From New Jersey, studying
environmental engineering.
- [Elizabeth] Great sweatshirt, Jjemba.
- [Anderson] He's a former
intern for Senator Cory Booker.
He says he's currently undecided
on who to support in 2020.
Eric?
- Hi, Senator.
- Good to see you, hi.
- Entitlements in this country,
though certainly not the
sexiest issue for Democratic candidates
to be discussing in this
race, are an area of concern
that under the status quo
will fail my generation.
Do you have a plan to reform our present
Social Security system to
increase its longevity?
- So I'm really glad you
asked about Social Security,
because this is one that reminds you
how things have broken
apart in this country.
As you all know, Social Security passed
back during the Great Depression.
The biggest problem with Social Security,
it was too narrow and cut
out too many, particularly,
jobs that were largely held by
African Americans and other groups.
But Social Security became a mainstay.
And from the 1930s until the late 1980s,
we understood that Social Security is
not something you can
just set once and go.
Population changes.
How long people live changes.
Women going back to work changes.
How many people get sick change, right?
And so every few years,
for a very long time,
we kept making little adjustments.
And that way, Social Security
stayed on a track to make sure
that it would be there for
your generation and the next
generation and the next
generation after that.
In the late 1980s, the
Republicans just said,
no, that we're not going
to make any more changes
to Social Security, not
going to increase the
revenue stream, not going
to change the pieces.
And we've been locked there.
And the consequence is
every year that goes by,
we get the system just a
little further out of whack.
Now, the good news is, we've got roughly,
I haven't checked the latest
numbers, but roughly about
20 more years where we
are if we do nothing.
And when it drops, it
would drop by roughly
about 25 percent, and then
level out and be there.
So it's not that it will
disappear for your generation.
But here's the deal.
This is one more of those
problems, a little like climate.
The sooner you fix it,
the easier it is to fix.
Now it's already hard on this front,
but it's one of those
things we need to fix now.
But the problem we've got is we're caught,
not in that nobody understands the math.
Everybody, well, not everybody
understands the math, but
there are a whole lot of
people who understand the math.
The problem is the political
will and the willingness
to step up and say, we've
got to make adjustments.
We've got to make adjustments on revenue.
We have to make adjustments,
I believe we need to bend
the curves, they're called,
so that particularly women
who had lower earnings for
so many years especially in
the first years that they
were working get better
support in their later years.
But at this moment,
there's no political
will to come together.
There's no one who's
willing to drive this.
Why?
Because Washington keeps
working for those at the top.
It's not working for people who
are relying on Social Security.
So your question was, is this something,
the plan is not hard.
It's political will to make it happen.
I'm willing to take on that fight.
It's an important fight.
So, thank you.
Thanks for the question.
(audience applauds)
- [Anderson] Our next
question comes from Max Frank.
He's a senior at Harvard,
studying social studies.
Max took a leave of absence
from college to work as a
full-time staffer for Hillary
Clinton's 2016 campaign.
Max?
- Hi, Max.
- Good evening, Senator Warren.
You know, as one of your constituents,
I just want to say thank
you for your service.
- Thank you.
- My question has to do with
the politics of this race.
In particular, I know
that you have experienced
President Trump's name-calling
and bullying firsthand.
And given the success that
he's had with these tactics
in the past, I was wondering
how you propose to counter
them if you were to become
the Democratic nominee.
And then, in particular, are
you worried that he might be
able to caricature you to
general election voters before
you've had a chance to
make your candidacy heard?
- So, thanks for the question.
You know, I've been
around this block before.
Back in 2012, when I ran
against that very popular
Republican incumbent,
he ran the same play.
And what I discovered at that
point is that around this
country, around the
commonwealth of Massachusetts,
people care a lot more
about their families than
they do about some kind of name-calling.
I got in the race in '12 and
I got in this race right now
as a presidential candidate
not because I looked at myself
in the mirror every day
and said, "Oh, Senator.
"President."
It wasn't that at all.
It's my life's work.
I grew up in a family that
was paycheck to paycheck.
I was one of those kids who had a dream.
We talked about college.
I've known what I wanted
to do since second grade.
I wanted to be a public school teacher.
Can we hear it for America's
public school teachers?
Come on, guys.
(audience applauds)
Yeah, I knew what I wanted to do.
But there was no money in my family.
And by the time I
graduated from high school,
there was no money even
for a college application,
much less to send me off
to four years of college.
So I have a kind of twisted
story, like some Americans do.
We're not all on a straight line on this.
And mine is that I won a scholarship.
Yay.
And then at 19, I fell in love.
And then I got married.
Yay.
And then I dropped out of school, yay.
And I took a job answering phones.
And I thought that was
going to be my life forever.
A good life, but not the dream I had.
And then I found a commuter college
that cost $50 a semester.
And for a price that I
could pay for on a part-time
waitressing job, I had a chance
to get a four-year diploma
and become a special needs teacher.
I have lived my dream.
And that's what I believe
is the best of America,
when we open more doors for more people.
I want to live in an America
that's not just about
opportunity for those born into privilege,
but that's about
opportunity for all of us.
And that's what we can do.
Just those few pieces I put together.
A 2 cent wealth tax would let
us do universal childcare,
would let us do universal Pre-K,
would let us do universal college,
would let us not back the
student loan debt burden,
and still have money to spend.
I think that this is the case we've
got to make against Donald Trump.
We're not going to win by
just saying not Donald Trump.
We're not going to win by doing
better name-calling than he does.
The way we're going to do
this is we're going to get out
and talk about our vision
and how it affects families
all across this country, how
it touches people personally.
And we're going to invite
people not just to vote but to
come off the sidelines
and be part of this,
to get engaged, to volunteer,
to kick in five bucks,
to go to elizabethwarren.com and sign up.
But it's every piece of this,
because what's at stake is
not only our economic future,
it is also our democracy.
And I'm in this fight all the way.
I think we make that case.
I think the American people are with us.
- We're going to have more
with Senator Elizabeth Warren,
a CNN special Democratic town hall event.
Stay with us.
(dramatic music)
- [Announcer] It's cedar-plank
seafood time at Red Lobster,
featuring three new dishes
that are planked to perfection.
Feast on new cedar-plank
lobster and shrimp.
Or new colossal shrimp and
salmon with a citrusy drizzle.
Tender, smokey and together on one plank.
But not for long, so hurry in.
(soft music)
- I'm okay.
(dramatic music)
- [Announcer] Pardon the
interruption but this is big.
Now at T-Mobile buy
any Samsung Galaxy S10,
get a Galaxy S10e free.
(keyboard clicks)
♪ Help, I need somebody ♪
♪ Help, not just anybody ♪
♪ Help, you know I need someone ♪
♪ Help ♪
♪ When I was younger, so
much younger than today ♪
♪ I never need, I never needed
anybody's help in any way ♪
♪ But now these days are gone ♪
♪ And I'm not so self assured ♪
♪ And now I find, now I
find I've changed my mind ♪
♪ And opened up the doors ♪
♪ Help me if you can I'm feeling down ♪
♪ And I do appreciate you being round ♪
♪ Help me get my feet back on the ground ♪
♪ Won't you please, please help me ♪
♪ Help me, help me oh ♪
- Thanks to Priceline
working with top airlines
to turn their unsold
seats into amazing deals
family reunion attendance is up.
- We're all related
- Yeah I see it.
And because Priceline offers great deals
by comparing thousands
of prices in real time
sports fans are seeing more away games.
(cheers)
Is that safe?
- Oh yeah.
- Not at all.
- No ma'am.
- Nope.
- And more people than ever
are enjoying romantic getaways.
That's gross.
Priceline, every trip is a big deal.
- [Announcer] Dr. Sanjay
Gupta voyages through one of
the darkest, coldest countries
in the world, Norway.
- And I'm the only one that's cold.
- [Announcer] And finds
some of the happiest people.
What's their secret?
Chasing Life, Saturday
May 4th at 9:00 Eastern.
- I had a lot of root canals, extractions,
always in dental pain.
I knew dentures would not be right for me
because I'm too active.
- I had a lot of cavities, root canals,
eating anything cold,
it would hurt so bad.
- I was embarrassed of my teeth.
I don't think dentures
were ever a solution.
The only option for me was Clear Choice.
- [Announcer] The Clear
Choice one day approach
is making dental implants a
reality for people all over
the country who suffer from
missing or failing teeth.
- Because we have the surgeon
and the prosthodontist
and the lab in one
facility working together
as a team we can perform
this procedure in one day.
- They put these beautiful
teeth in my mouth
and I can eat ice cream, I can eat steak.
- [Announcer] Schedule your
free consultation today,
we'll even talk about financing options.
- I went to Clear Choice for new teeth
and I got so much more,
they changed my life.
- Get at least five or six
compliments a day at work
and go, "Wow, those
teeth, they're gorgeous."
All because of Clear Choice.
- [Announcer] Call Clear Choice today.
- [Announcer] The Redemption
Project with Van Jones
premiers Sunday at 9:00 on CNN.
- Welcome back.
We're live in New Hampshire for a special
CNN Democratic presidential
town hall even.
Continuing now with
Senator Elizabeth Warren of Massachusetts.
I want to, our next question
is about climate change.
- Good.
- You talked about it briefly.
It's drastically grown as a
top issue among young voters,
according to a Harvard Institute
of Politics youth poll,
which was released today.
This is Tyler Pearce,
a freshman at the
University of New Hampshire.
He's studying biomedical science,
which I'm not even sure what
that means because I'm dumb.
He worked as a fellow for the
New Hampshire Democratic
Party for the 2018 midterms.
Tyler?
- Hi, Tyler.
- Hi, Senator, how are you?
- I'm good, how about you?
- Good.
So my question is, what
will you do to combat
climate change in a world where the threat
has become increasingly more dangerous?
- All right, Tyler,
it is the existential question right now.
As I said, I was just out in
three different states facing
climate, the effects of climate
change in different ways,
but all of them potentially devastating.
I have an 8-year-old grandson,
and I think about what the
world is going to be like when he's 38.
Will it be a place where our cities
are underwater part of the time?
Will it be a place where
the Midwest has burned up,
where we have lost some
of our great forests?
Will it be a place where the oceans,
large parts of the oceans are dead?
Will it be a place where people around
the world are just
fighting for clean water?
We're running out of time to make change.
We must make change.
And we must make it now.
So here's how I see this,
I am a strong supporter
of the Green New Deal.
(audience applauds)
And I want to tell you why.
There are two principal reasons for that.
The first reason that I'm a strong
supporter is it is a way to say urgency.
Now, we cannot wait any longer.
We have got to make change.
That's how I hear this.
The second part about the
Green New Deal right now is
it calls for a huge investment
in our infrastructure.
And I think that's just
absolutely critical.
And when I say our infrastructure,
it's about our green infrastructure,
it's about our power infrastructure,
but it's also about
hardening our infrastructure
so that we can withstand heavier storms,
so that flooding is not so much a problem,
so that we move to distributed
generation of power.
Lots of pieces that we need to do.
But I also see this as a time
when it's all hands on deck,
that is, we need to do everything we can.
So let me just do a
couple that a president of
the United States can do all by herself.
And that is, part one,
I just put out a plan.
On the first day of my administration,
I will put in place a moratorium,
no new drilling, no new mining
on any federal lands, period.
(audience applauds)
We should not be selling out for pennies
on the dollar to mining companies
and to oil companies
our national treasures.
I'll give you another just little
piece of this, and that is 10,000 jobs.
For people who want to go
spend a year in the national
parks, in the national
forests, to be able to give
something back to the land
and to make some repairs.
This is a part of what we can do together.
How about a couple of more pieces?
The United States is a
world leader on climate.
We are. We're just leading in
the wrong direction right now.
And that's dangerous,
because it's not only
what we're doing wrong.
It's that we're giving cover
to the rest of the world
for everybody who doesn't
want to have to step up,
who doesn't want to have
to take the tough steps,
who doesn't want to have to
make changes in their economy.
We're giving them cover.
That stops on the first
day of my administration.
We become a world leader in the
direction of a sustainable Earth.
That's where we go.
And, by the way, can I
throw in just one more?
I know.
And that is no coal lobbyists
for head of the EPA.
(audience applauds)
- All right, we have time for,
we have time for one more
question from the audience.
This is Nicholas Fahy.
He's a freshman at Harvard
from Massachusetts.
Nicholas?
- Hi, Nicholas.
- Hi.
As a Democrat who has a lot
of respect and admiration
for President Obama but
who also knows that,
like every president,
he had his shortcomings,
what do you think is the
biggest philosophical difference
the way you would approach
your job as president
and the way that President
Obama approached his job?
- You know, I'm going to take this in just
a little bit different
direction, if I can.
No, no, I'm going to get here.
So I spent, as I've
told all of you, really,
my whole life's work about what's
happening to working families.
And starting in the early
2000s, the crisis was coming.
I was waving my arms, ringing the bell,
doing everything I could.
I said families are getting
cheated all over this country.
It started when the mortgage companies
targeted communities of color.
They targeted seniors.
They targeted Latinos.
They came in and sold the
worst possible mortgages
and stripped wealth out
of those communities,
and then took those
products across the nation.
I went everywhere I could.
I talked about it to
anyone who would listen,
a crisis is coming.
And I'll just say,
nobody wanted to hear it.
Really basically what
happened in Washington,
nobody could hear it.
I learned, if your ears
are stuffed with money,
it's hard to hear.
So the crisis hit in 2007,
2008, and just took us down.
The big question becomes,
so what are you going to do going forward?
And a lot of folks thought
what we should do is we should
just take care of the big
financial institutions.
My view was, we've got to
put a cop on the beat to make
sure that this never happens
to working families again.
So the idea I had, Consumer
Financial Protection Bureau,
I said, I'm going to get in this fight.
I was a college professor.
I have no political sway,
but I'm going to get in
this fight and I'm going to fight for it.
And here was the deal.
People told me two things.
Great idea.
Don't even try.
And the reason not to try is
there is no way on God's green
Earth you will ever get this
passed, because the giant
financial institutions will
fight you every inch of the way.
- [Anderson] We've got to wrap it up.
- All right.
So here's what happened.
I got in the fight.
President Obama signed it into law.
And he was the one who stood
there when everyone else said
in his administration, throw
that agency under the bus.
And he said, no, I'm not
going to let this crisis pass
and not come away with a
consumer agency that makes sure
that families never get cheated again.
I will always be grateful
to the president for that.
- [Anderson] Senator Elizabeth Warren.
Up next, Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders.
We'll be right back.
(audience applauds and cheers)
(soft music)
- [Announcer] Everyone's
gotta listen to mom.
When it comes to reducing the
sugar in your family's diet
Coke, Dr Pepper and Pepsi hear you
and we're working
together to do just that.
Bringing you more great tasting
beverages with less
sugar or no sugar at all.
Smaller portion sizes.
Clear calorie labels
and reminders to think balance.
Because we know mom wants what's best.
More beverage choices,
smaller portions, less sugar,
balanceus.org.
- I like to make my life easy.
Romo Mode.
Good luck with that one.
Yes!
That's why I wear Sketchers slip ons.
They're effortless, just
slim them right on and off.
Sketchers slip ons, with
Air Cooled memory foam.
- [Announcer] Allergies with
sinus congestion and pressure?
You won't find relief here.
Go to the pharmacy counter
for powerful Claritin-D.
While the leading allergy spray
only relieves six symptoms
Claritin-D relievers eight,
including sinus congestion and pressure.
Claritin-D relieves more.
- Uh oh, looks like someone's still
nervous about buying a new house.
- Is it that obvious?
- Yes it is.
You know maybe you'd worry
less if you got Geico
to help with your homeowners insurance.
- I didn't know Geico helps
with homeowners insurance.
- Yeah, they've been doing it for years.
What are you doing?
Big Steve?
- Thanks man.
- There he is.
- [Announcer] Get to know
Geico and see how much you
could save on homeowners
and renters insurance.
- Your patio is so cozy.
- Oh well, our yard could
really use some work.
Do you know any good landscapers?
- Oh you know, I think I do.
- Oh I'd love to take your advice
but I need quotes from your top four guys
and check their credentials
and customer reviews.
Oh and I would like to get
them started this week.
- [Announcer] You can't
expect your neighbors
to do everything Home Advisor can.
So to find and instantly book the right
pro at a fair price just ask Home Advisor.
- [Announcer] This is an apple.
Some people might try to
tell you that it's a banana.
They might scream
"Banana, banana, banana,"
over and over and over again.
They put banana in all caps.
You might even start to
believe that this is a banana.
But it's not.
This is an apple.
- [Announcer] If your moderate
to severe ulcerative colitis
or Crohn's symptoms are holding you back
and your current treatment
hasn't worked well enough
it may be time for a change.
As your doctor about Entyvio,
the only biologic developed
and approved just for UC and Crohn's.
Entyvio works at the site of
inflammation in the GI tract
and is clinically proven
to help many patients
achieve both symptom relief and remission.
Infusion and serious
allergic reactions can happen
during or after treatment.
Entyvio may increase risk of infection,
which can be serious.
PML, a rare serious, potentially
fatal brain infection
caused by a virus may be possible.
Tell your doctor if you have an infection,
experience frequent infections
or have flue like symptoms or sores.
Liver problems can occur with Entyvio.
If you're.