- Lawyers or YouHaveALawyer.com.
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-LAWYERS
or visit YouHaveALawyer.com.
If you have a phone, you have a lawyer.
♪ The one and only TV 9 ♪
(percussive techno music)
- [Announcer] This is Daily Blast Live.
We are talking about what
you're talking about.
- 'Cause everyone's talking about this.
- [Announcer] Always live,
always real, always unpredictable.
- You are totally off-base here!
- [Announcer] Log on and
join our live conversation.
- I can't believe I'm saying
this, I do agree with you.
- [Announcer] DBL starts right now.
(lively music)
- [Director] Three, two.
- Welcome to DBL.
It's Wednesday, February 13th.
We are live and we are talking about
what you're talking about.
I'm here with Tory, Jeff, Al, and I'm Sam.
And if you haven't noticed,
we have a very special guest co-host.
You all know him as Dr. Drew Pinsky,
but you're so much more to me.
I know you've heard this
a gazillion times by now
but you're not only a
friend, you're my mentor,
and I really do owe sitting
in this chair to you.
So, thank you.
- There's a reason we worked with you.
You're good.
- Aww, Drew!
- So that's that.
- That means so much to me.
- [Al] Emergency fallout.
(everyone laughs)
- Wow, Al.
Geez!
- I love some Sammy.
- Okay, it's harsh.
- Well, thank you for
being here, Dr. Drew.
We begin with an update to
a story we've been tracking.
Empire star Jussie Smollett
is hitting back at reports
that he has changed his story,
or has not been fully
cooperative with police
who are investigating his alleged attack.
Jussie's reps released a
statement that says in part,
"Chicago PD has repeatedly informed us
"that they find Jussie's account
"of what happened that night
consistent and credible.
"Superintendent Johnson has been clear
"from day one that Jussie is a victim."
This comes a day after a spokesperson
for the Chicago Police Department said
that the phone records
that Jussie turned over,
"Do not meet the burden for
a criminal investigation
"as they were limited
and heavily redacted."
Now, Jussie's reps contend
that information was redacted
to protect the privacy
of personal contacts
and other high-profile people
who had nothing to do with the attack,
and tomorrow, Jussie is sitting down
with GMA's Robin Roberts
in what looks to be
a highly emotional interview.
Check out this teaser.
- At any point during the attack,
did you fear for your life?
- [Jeff] I'm good.
- So, very emotional interview.
Dr. Drew, I know on your radio show,
you've been following
this case in and out.
What would you say to
the narrative out there
that's pushing that he
may be making this up?
- Yeah, I just think
everyone needs to calm down
and not grab onto any narrative.
It's not our job to create a narrative,
it's the Chicago PD's
to figure out the facts
and put that narrative together
and then tell us what the deal is.
Something happened to him.
If he has overstated it for some reason,
I'm also still worried about him
and what happened that made
him distort this thing.
So, all of us sit back and
just let this thing play out.
It's not our business!
This mob action that we always
get into drives me insane.
- And Tory, you've had a
pretty strong take on this.
- Yeah, I mean, but
you have to understand,
innocent until proven guilty
is because we believe in America,
that we believe our victims at first.
And if it's not true, Dr. Drew's right,
there might be something else wrong.
But at this point, imagine
had he let us see his phone.
We're already this way and
we haven't seen anything.
I mean, Tom Brady didn't give up his phone
when it was Deflategate and
yet, we're jumping on this guy.
I agree with Dr. Drew.
Let's just put a pause on
everything for a second.
- Yeah, fair enough, I agree.
- I think anything that
we get from this story
will help push your narrative.
There's money to be made from Division.
- Oh, boy.
- So, if--
- [Drew] You're breaking my heart.
- Yes, unfortunately it's
the world we live in.
(Drew scoffs)
If this is proven to be a hoax,
now all the conspiracy theorists now go,
and you know what else was a hoax?
- Right.
- Sandy Hook.
- Parkland.
- The Moon!
- Sandy Hooks, the Pizzagate,
and so if it's not,
then there's other places will be like,
see, we're under attack.
So, it's like, everybody
has, unfortunately,
a financial interest in
how this story turns out.
I guarantee you a lot of
people commenting on this
are not fans of his,
and don't care about
his physical wellbeing.
They just see him, or the
kid at the National Museum
with the Native American,
as just a way to further--
- Their agenda.
- Further their agenda.
- I just encourage people, if
there are holes in your story,
you think there's holes in
his story, which I don't,
watch the interview and
make up your own opinion.
Don't listen to what
people are writing online.
- So wait for tomorrow.
We will definitely be covering
the interview tomorrow.
- Absolutely.
- I agree.
- But I don't wanna emphasize Al's point.
The media out there creates narrative.
We're having a conversation about it
but you with those headlines
that take a specific position,
one way or the other,
that is for the good of the network
that is giving you the
narrative and nothing else.
- They wanna capture your
eyes so they can make money.
- Right.
- As you said.
- They figure out what you wanna hear
and they keep feeding it to ya.
- Be an independent thinker, please,
and chime in, DBL Nation, we
wanna hear from you as well.
Well, we finally have some good news
coming out of Washington, D.C. right now.
Let's get to Kelly
Schuberth with the latest.
- Sam, we're just two days away
from another partial government shutdown,
but it looks like the president
may now stop that from happening.
We told you about a tentative deal
that congressional negotiators
came up with Monday night.
Trump said he wasn't happy with the deal,
but Today's sources say that
he is expected to sign it.
In the meantime, Senator Ted Cruz
is backing a different plan
to get the President the
money he wants for his wall.
Cruz sent this Tweet saying
we should use the money U.S. prosecutors
are seeking from now-convicted El Chapo.
They're seeking 14 billion in
drug profits and other assets,
and Cruz says that money
should go towards securing the border.
Sam, I'll keep you updated.
- Thank you so much, Kelly.
Well, we have a new top dog.
Meet King, the Fox Terrier.
Look at his beard!
(laughing) Took home the
Best in Show Award last night
at the Westminster Dog
Show in New York City.
Competition was rough, but once again,
the Fox Terrier won the top prize.
This marks the 15th time that
breed has come out on top,
much more than any other.
Bono the Havanese took second.
- They were robbed!
- [Sam] But many were upset
that the fan-favorite,
a Longhaired Dachshund named Burns,
Tory's favorite, did not win.
And in a socking turn of events,
the Schipperke named Colton,
who won the Non-Sporting
Group, was disqualified--
- Scandal!
- [Sam] The moment before the judging
due to a conflict of interest.
Other top dogs include Baby
Lars, who won the Herding Group.
He's a Bouvier des Flandres.
(everyone laughs)
- [Drew] Bouvier des Flandres.
(hosts laughing)
And great pronunciation on that.
I thought I was back in France.
(hosts laughing)
- And this Sussex Spaniel named Bean,
who won the Sporting Group,
and finally meet Wilma, the Boxer,
who took home the Gold
for the Working Group.
But it wasn't just us humans
who enjoyed watching the dog competition.
Check out all these dogs who
really got into the action.
Tory, I know, now first of
all, scandal really, Tory?
- Big scandal.
- What?
- Big Scandal.
- No!
- The Schipperke was
in it, and guess what?
They shook hands with the judge and said,
"I need you to leave."
That is huge in the dog world, am I right?
- I don't know.
- He does know.
- I had to do the shaking
hands, like they're gonna kiss,
and then you're gonna go--
- And then it was.
- Wait, do we know why?
- Yes, because the judge
was a co-owner of said dog.
- Ugh.
Oh, no!
- It was an owner
eligibility issue.
- Shouldn't that be illegal?
- Well, it was.
He did a nice lap and then he walked.
- Oh.
- I just have to say this,
the Wire, I know you're a dog-person.
- I am a dog-person.
- The Wire Fox Terrier
has won 15 times, okay?
The bearded guy that looks like Sherlock?
- He's Beerlock.
- He looks like a guy.
- He looks like a guy, right?
- I wouldn't want him
in my bedroom when I'm dressing.
- And I'm not saying this
'cause I own a Dachshund.
At some point, that
Dachshund was on that night,
and he stood like this,
and he and the crowd--
- Okay.
- Okay, sorry.
- Can I get a one-shot on
Tory while she does that?
Do it, Tory.
- [Tory] Okay, so.
- This is the Dachshund, one-shot on Tory.
- [Al] Please don't put
me in it, there you go.
(hosts laughing)
- Thank you. (clapping)
- And he shoulda won!
- Well done, well done.
- And win that,
but it was Madison Square Garden!
Thank you everyone, thank you.
- Wow, look at Jeff.
- It's crazy!
- Hey, could we move past this?
- Yeah, so angry!
- We covered this story
more than the Super Bowl.
- He's so angry.
- This is insane.
- Can somebody explain to me
why I watch it religiously
every year after the Macy's
Parade on Thanksgiving?
Is this a recorded version?
- It's such a tradition!
- No, this is Westminster.
The other one is another one.
- That's the National Dog Show.
- Yes, exactly, correct.
- This is the Westminster.
But this is the more
prestigious one, right?
- A bit, yes.
- I think it's
a little antiquated.
- Oh!
- It is, completely.
- They should have
rescue dogs only.
- And they do.
They have a whole separate
one for rescue but I--
- Yes, they call it The
One People Don't Watch.
(Tory laughing)
- Yeah, I like the
beautiful dogs, come on now.
- Okay, wow!
- 'Cause you wouldn't have
to buy one, it's just.
- Oh, how fun was it.
- I'm with you.
- Coming up on DBL, Dr. Drew
answers your burning questions
about love and relationships.
Also ahead, we'll tell
you why you shouldn't mess
with country singer, Miranda Lambert.
One woman learned that
lesson the hard way.
Plus, actor Anson Williams tells us
how John Lennon changed the lives
of the cast and crew of Happy Days.
Don't miss Tory's one-on-one interview.
And Esquire magazine is in the center
of a fire-storm over this cover.
We'll tell you why a little later.
(lively music)
- [Announcer] This February,
Daily Blast Live and Sandals Resorts
want you to fall in love all over again.
We're giving away a trip for
you and your special someone
to one of Sandal's luxury
included vacation hotspots.
All you need to do is watch
DBL for the Word of the Day
and go to
dailybalstlive.com/sandals to enter.
The more words, the more chances to win.
The winner will be announced
live on DBL February 27th.
How could you not love that?
- [Announcer] Best Fiends.
(triumphant music)
Collect Jo-Jo and tons
of other cute characters.
(spray can whooshing)
Solve thousands of fun puzzles.
Download Best Fiends for free today.
That's friends without the R.
Best Fiends.
(triumphant music)
Collect Howie and tons
of other cute characters.
Solve thousands of fun puzzles.
Download Best Fiends for free today.
That's friends without the R.
Best Fiends.
(lively music)
- [Announcer] Next ET.
- It's been a roller coaster.
- [Announcer] Britney Spears
on her father's health crisis.
What we just learned and will she ever
return to her Vegas residency?
Next ET.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Tonight at 7:30 on WUSA9.
- [Announcer] Diamonds at
their lowest price in years.
1/2 carat Solitaires are now $399.
One carat, $790.
Two carat, $950 per carat.
Plus one carat studs, $399.
Insane prices of thousands
of GIA diamonds and designer rings.
Buy Direct, The Jewelry Exchange Bethesda!
- [Announcer] Get new floors
during Empire Today's
gigantic 75% off sale.
That's carpet, laminate
and even hardwood 75% off.
Empire makes getting
beautiful, new floors easy.
See samples in your home,
get a free estimate,
and have your floors
professionally installed.
Update your floors with Empire
and get 75% off carpet,
laminate and hardwood.
Schedule now!
♪ 800-588-2300 Empire ♪
- [Announcer] Today.
- [Narrator] Stronger is
rebuilding a newborn's heart
and restoring a father's faith.
It's standing tall after
one surgery, not six.
Stronger is being a typical
kid, despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding it earlier
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is seeking answers
and not giving up until you find them.
Because we don't just
want your kids to grow up.
We want them to grow up stronger.
- [Announcer] Diamonds
The Jewelry Exchange
has certified 1/2 carat for $690,
one carat $1,790, two carat $5,900.
Certified Lab Grown at
over 50% off wholesale rap,
plus thousands of GIA diamonds
at the guaranteed lowest price.
Buy Factory Direct, The
Jewelry Exchange Bethesda.
- Your kids tell me that you lock them
out of the house in the cold.
- Not ever, no.
- If she's being honest, step forward.
If she's feeding you a
bunch of bull, step back.
- [Narrator] New Dr. Phil.
- [Announcer] Today at four,
followed by WUSA9 News at five.
(lively tecnno music)
- Welcome back to DBL.
As you know, we have a very
special guest in studio today.
He's a board certified physician
and addiction medicine specialist.
You know him from
Loveline, Dr. Drew On Call,
and Celebrity Rehab.
He's my dear friend.
Welcome Dr. Drew Pinsky.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah!
- Yes!
(everyone clapping)
- Pleasure to be here, guys.
- [Sam] And this is exciting because--
- Only, you traumatized me with
those pictures, but thanks.
(hosts laughing)
- Well, we, this is important
because a lot of our viewers at home,
you guys love Dr. Drew,
his advice on addiction and relationships,
but today we're focusing on relationships.
- Okay.
- We've asked our viewers
to send in their love-related questions
for a segment we're calling
Dear DBL, with Dr. Drew.
So let's get started.
Al, let's take the first one.
- [Al] All right!
It says, "Wanting More in Saint Louis:
"My bedroom life with
my girlfriend sucks!"
- Uh-oh.
- Okay!
- [Al] "And we're only in the first year
"of our relationship.
"Three times a week if I'm lucky.
"Am I the bad guy for wanting
"to break up with her over this?"
- Okay, well mismatched sexual desire
is a very common thing.
Three times a week, above
average by the way, not bad.
- She doing good!
- I'd say Tory and Sam
do a little bit like
oh, what the hell here.
- What?
- How much this guy want
but that is mismatched sexual desire
- That's above average?
- Yeah.
- [Sam] Well, what about
it being the first year?
- Above average.
Average in long-term relationship
is about 1 1/2, two times a week, average.
- But what about a new
relationship like this?
- We just learned something about Al, too.
Just make that known.
(hosts laughing)
- [Al] If not twice a
day, it wasn't a day.
- Oh, Lord, Al!
- Right and some people
are at that rate, that's for sure.
- Yeah.
- And people have
to reach a compromise.
- What?
- See, we just learned
something about Jeff, too.
(hosts laughing)
- If twice a day is not a day,
how do you get anything done?
- There's this thing called
morning and night, Jeff.
- Yeah, I love sleep.
- A lot is revealed just in
answering these questions,
but it's about compromising
and you have to be able to tell her
that this is not your rate
and you have to step it up.
There may be things contributing to that.
We don't think about this,
and one of the things
that I see most commonly in young couples,
when a female sexual desire
is not matching a man,
she may be on a high
progesterone birth control pill
and that suppresses their libido
and doctors don't tell 'em about that.
So take a look at your birth control.
The progesterones can really
be working against you.
- Good to know.
- That's amazing.
- Wow.
- This guy!
- I know!
(laughing)
He's like a fountain of knowledge.
Ellie Mae writes,
"I'm in a marriage where my
husband gambles compulsively
"and frequents gentleman's clubs."
- Uh-oh.
- "After 34 years of marriage,
"we are drowning in debt."
- Oh!
- Oh, boy.
- "Should I walk out?"
This is Ellie Mae.
- So, Ellie Mae, this is for real.
Ellie Mae?
- Yeah.
- Like from the Beverly Hillbillies?
- It's amazing.
- Burt, that was for you.
(hosts laughing)
So, yeah, this is really,
this is a tragedy.
And this is a great example of
how real gambling addiction,
when you really see it, it destroys lives.
There may be some sexual
addiction in here, too.
He's going to gentleman clubs.
You have to decide if
you're gonna leave or not.
I'd for sure go to a
program called Al-Anon,
which is support for those
and loved one's with
addictions of various types.
There's specific ones for
gambling and sex addicts,
but Al-Anon's easier to find
and then think about what
you wanna do with this.
But absolutely, he gets
treatment or you leave
is a very reasonable position to be in.
- Wow.
- Wow, that's good to hear.
- Sad.
- Ruth in Louisvile writes,
"I'm dating someone
going through a divorce.
"We both feel strongly about each other,
"but she's not ready for
a relationship right now.
"Yet, we both can't
stop seeing each other,
"and it feels more like a rebound.
"Is our timing setting us up to fail?"
- And, but I gotta answer,
finish up on that last question, too.
He goes to gamblers, like
GA, Gambler's Anonymous.
Or SLA, Sex and Love Addicts Anonymous,
Sex Addicts Anonymous, back to this one.
This is Trevor, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Is that him?
No, it's not.
- Yup.
- No, yes, Trevor?
- This is Ruth.
- Oh, Ruth.
- Ruth.
- Ruth, I'm...
When somebody's going through a divorce,
you don't wanna get hooked
into a long-term relationship.
You wanna wait 'til that's
all over with and behind them.
You're more of a life-preserver
when somebody is going through
that kind of a horrible
crisis in their life.
We need a lot more information
to kinda tease it out for you, but I--
- [Sam] Could it work out?
- It could, but I got
bad feelings about this.
- Whoa, okay.
- Yeah.
- Interesting.
- Mm.
- That's you, Jeff, it's your turn.
- I just read Ruth.
- I'll read Trevor in Tampa.
- Oh, geez!
- Boom!
- Trevor in Tampa said,
"My girlfriend gets mad at me--
- [Jeff] That'll teach you
how to handle my business up there.
- [Drew] I love it!
(hosts laughing)
"For not posting pictures of
us together on social media.
"I like to post about my
hobbies, not relationships,
"but she thinks I'm hiding her.
"Who is in the wrong here?"
- [Sam] That's a relatable one.
- It is a relatable one, and, ugh.
You, sir.
You, sir, need to step up
because she's letting you
know something very simple
that could make her very happy,
and why wouldn't you do that
if you know it's something
that really would help somebody
or make her feel good and she's
somebody you say you love,
why wouldn't you wanna do that?
- Amen.
- Wow!
- Amen!
- Drew, quickly,
what's wrong with our
dysfunctional family?
- Yeah, what's wrong here?
- Yes!
- I'm mostly worried
about you and Sam, Jeff.
(hosts laughing)
That's where I see the trouble.
- I'm off the hook!
- Yeah.
- Tory?
- They're all doin' pretty good.
- Al?
I don't know about that.
- Well, I'm normal.
- All right.
- Everybody says I'm the normal one.
- Sure, okay.
- We heard a little
(stammering) you're above normal
in certain areas, Al, just saying.
- [Hosts] Oh!
- I get that a lot.
- We found that out
10 minutes ago, five minutes ago.
- Coming up on DBL, a lot of people
are saying Esquire
magazine missed the mark
with this cover story.
We'll tell you what all
the commotion is about.
And talk about a throw back.
Actor Anson Williams from Happy Days
settles the score once and for all.
So, who's cooler, Potsie or the Fonz?
Come on now, the Fonz.
He tells our own Tory Schulmen next.
- [Tory] It was Potsie.
(lively music)
(transitions to lullaby music)
- Shh, that's it.
Sleep tight, little one.
- Thanks, mom.
You take such good care of him.
- That's what grandmas do.
- I don't know what we'd do without you.
- Well, I made sure you'll
have help even after I'm gone.
- After you're gone?
Mom, are you okay?
- Everything is fine.
Just so you know, I got
a life insurance policy,
so when the time comes, I won't
leave you a financial mess.
Let's face it.
There will be a funeral,
and maybe medical bills.
It's not an inheritance or anything,
but it will help cover my expensenses.
- I don't wanna think about that.
- Well, you don't have to.
I already took care of it.
And with this policy, I can
earn discounts, get rewards,
and even get tips on how to live healthy.
That could help me be around even longer
for that little guy.
- [Narrator] Final expense life insurance
with guaranteed acceptance
from John Hancock
can help people aged
60 to 80 sleep easier.
It helps your family take
care of funeral costs,
medical bills, and other debts.
The average funeral alone is
between $8,000 and $9,000.
Without insurance, could
your family pay the bill?
Final Expense Life Insurance can help,
and acceptance is guaranteed
with no medical questions or exams.
Rates start around $13 a month
and policies range from $2,000 to $20,000,
so you can select the best
fit for your needs and budget.
Here's another guarantee.
Payments never go up
and coverage never goes down
for as long as you live.
It also comes with confidence.
For more than 150 years,
John Hancock has helped meet the needs
of more than 18 million customers.
Plus, you can earn discounts, get rewards,
and receive healthy living tips
through the John Hancock Vitality program.
Best of all, it's easy.
You can apply by phone or online.
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-978-0663
or go online to learn more
about Final Expense Life Insurance
with guaranteed acceptance.
That's 1-800-978-0663.
- [Announcer] Today's Watch
and Win word is sunglasses.
(percussive music)
- Welcome back to DBL.
All month long, I am talking
with TV legends from the past
to find out where they are now.
So, I headed to The Hollywood Museum
in the heart of Los Angeles, California
and sat down with Anson Williams,
better known as Potsie from
♪ Monday, Tuesday, Happy Days ♪
Check it out.
(lively orchestral music)
♪ Monday, Tuesday, I'm in heaven ♪
(laughing) It was very, very good opening.
I am here with someone
that I've always had a secret crush on
and now it's not so secret.
It's Anson Williams of Happy Days.
Hello, how are you?
- I am good.
Those are original lyrics.
- [Tory] I was gonna say.
- I haven't heard those lyrics before.
- Never heard that before, it's amazing.
You play one of the most
iconic characters ever on TV.
Do you have a favorite memory?
- Actually the best
memories aren't on the show,
they're off the show.
We had a softball team and
we went all over the world.
- [Tory] Get outta here!
What was your team name?
- Let me guess!
Happy Days!
- Happy Days!
That was very clever.
- I like how original that was.
- Yeah, it was, do ya like that?
- [Tory] So, you were best friends
with Richie Cunningham, Ron Howard.
We also have Fonzie, Henry Winkler.
We wanna know straight up,
which one made you laugh harder?
- Oh, Henry, yeah.
He's a genius.
There's no words for it.
Just universal hysterics.
Look at the character he created, Fonzie.
That was not written.
- [Tory] Do you still keep
in touch with these guys?
- We do!
- Yes?
- We do.
- That makes me happy.
- [Anson] We've been friends forever.
- Now, a lot of people actually told me
they had crushes on you,
but Fonzie was sort of the cool guy.
Did Potsie ever wanna be Fonzie?
- Who would not wanna be Fonzie?
(Tory laughing)
Are you kidding?
Let's be truthful!
- Let's be honest, here.
- All right?
Come on!
Oh, no, I like Potsie better.
What?
Shoot me now.
- I heard that maybe one
of The Beatles came by?
- A couple of The Beatles.
- Tell me about that,
'cause I think I'm all
(screams) about this.
- I was (screams) about that.
(Tory laughing)
You're on a set, Happy Days.
There's a guy standing
by the coffee machine
that looks just like Jonh Lennon
in sunglasses and some kid,
and Donny goes, "Oh, yeah.
"John Lennon came here to
hang out with us (laughs)."
It was John Lennon who came
here to hang out with us.
You bet.
The nicest, kindest, shyest guy.
He's doing doodles for, like literally,
original John Lennon
doodles for the crew--
- You know how much those are worth?
- Yeah, for the crew.
Not us, oh no, we're professionals.
We don't ask for anything.
The crew bought houses
with the freakin' picture.
(Tory laughing)
I haven't told anyone.
On this show will be the first.
- Exclusive!
- And this just happened.
It's exclusive, four,
five, six months ago?
There's this very nice looking man.
So I'm sitting there and
all of a sudden I hear,
"Excuse me, I don't mean to interrupt."
It was Julian Lennon.
(Tory laughs)
- [Tory] I'm sorry, I don't mean to--
- 40 years later.
- Oh my god!
- [Anson] Can we take a selfie?
40 years later, it all came around.
- [Tory] That's a great story.
- True story.
- That's a crazy story.
I think all the millennials
know Buy One Get One
which is my favorite thing
in the whole wide world.
You found a way to curate
it all in one area.
- You bet.
- Tell me about that.
- It's called BOGOlist.com.
The best BOGO's are there, have fun.
Not only is it the lottery win every time,
it's the best deals on the internet.
- Thank you Anson Wilson
for taking the time.
It's been amazing, thank you so, so much.
- Thank you.
(pleasant music)
- Subscribe to our YouTube channel
at YouTube.com/DailyBlastLive
to check out an extended interview
where Anson and I discuss
his product, Alert Drops.
It's a simple solution
to combat drowsy driving
and it can save lives.
We'll be right back.
(lighthearted music)
- [Announcer] Promotional consideration
is brought to you by.
- [Announcer] If a dirty
CPAP is making you sick,
you're not alone.
- I was getting sinus infections
because I wasn't cleaning my CPAP properly
and that continued until I got my SoClean.
- [Announcer] SoClean is the world's
first automated CPAP
cleaner and sanitizer.
It kills 99.9% of all
CPAP germs and bacteria
that can build up in your
mask, hose, and reservoir.
- I don't have to push
a button or anything.
I just put the mask in the chamber,
close the lid, and it runs automatically.
SoClean has been a life-saver.
- [Announcer] SoClean works
on all popular CPAP machines and masks.
Try it risk-free for 30 days.
Even shipping is free.
Call 1-800-418-0640
to take advantage of
this limited time offer.
- I would recommend the
SoClean machine to anyone else.
It is that good of a machine.
It has made that big a
difference in my life.
- [Woman] Try SoClean
risk-free for 30 days.
Even shipping is free.
Call 1-800-418-0640 or go to SoClean.com.
- [Man] What is Verify?
- Hi, I keep seeing stories about felons
that are running for Congress.
Could you verify?
- [Narrator] Verify.
A new way to separate fact from fiction.
You ask the questions,
Verify will do the digging
with full transparency.
- We went to a political
science professor.
A reverse-image search led us to this.
He's a felon!
Nicole, yeah, we can Verify that for you.
- [Announcer] Verify.
Look into it.
(bouncy music)
- Well, cooking in my kitchen
before was pretty archaic,
so we went to Joe at Cabinet Discounters.
He was able to design it and lay it out.
But he laid out a very
functional kitchen for us.
The term discounted to me is just a word.
And, they really designed
a nice kitchen for us
and it absolutely met our expectations.
We've actually gone back
twice and had work done.
We certainly would recommend
it to any of our friends.
- [Man] Get a free consultation
with an experienced designer.
Call 1-800-THE-DREAM or
visit cabinetdiscounters.com.
- With Cox, you can watch all your movies
and shows whatever the weather.
(thunder rumbling)
(people chattering)
With DirecTV, heavy rain or
snow can affect your signal.
(thunder rumbling)
(family sighs)
It's clear that Cox is the better choice,
just like it's clear
that the make-up artist
is still learning the ropes.
(man coughs)
(thunder rumbling)
(host sighing)
(lively music)
- Unlike DirecTV, Cox
works in any weather.
Get Contour TV and high speed
internet for $79.99 a month.
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm Dan from MarketPro Homebuyers,
and we wanna buy your home.
Don't make repairs, don't pay commissions,
and don't wait another day.
We'll get you the cash you need.
No agent fees, no closing costs.
We'll even help you
pack and move for free.
For a no obligation offer,
call 301-799-S-E-L-L.
That's 301-799-7355, or visit
marketprohomebuyers.com.
We buy houses as-is or on your schedule.
Call today.
- [Announcer] Live tonight.
- I'm like crazy.
- [Announcer] Celebrity Big
Brother finale week continues.
- We're the final five!
- [Announcer] Don't miss the
ultimate celebrity showdown.
- We are fighting like Put Bulls.
- [Announcer] Who will wow the jury?
- It's not over yet.
- [Announcer] And win it all?
- Heller?
Who's on the phone?
It's winning!
Oh, it's for me?
- [Announcer] Celebrity Big Brother
live season finale tonight.
- [Narrator] This Thursday could be
the most romantic night ever.
- A Valentine's dinner with my mother.
Is this the saddest moment of my life?
- No.
- Not even close.
- [Announcer] New Mom Thursday.
(upbeat music)
- Welcome back to DBL.
Now, whether you're more of a date night,
or the gift-giving type on Valentines Day,
my girl Tory and I have some tips
in this edition of DBL Drive.
You know who it is!
It's presented by CarShield.
(electronic music)
Tory, I gotta ask you.
What's a perfect Valentines
Day for Tory Shulton?
- I just don't get it together,
so at the very end of the day,
I'm writing a coupon for a hug,
you know what I mean?
Like, I'm like here's a coupon for--
- Here's a coupon book.
I'll clean the guest bathroom, whatever.
- [Tory] What about you?
- All right, I'm just
gonna get this out there.
I think Valentine's Day is embarrassing.
I got a pizza, but I cut
it in the shape of a heart.
Oh, no.
- (laughing) What?
- That's because that's something
that no human being would
ever do that really loves you.
- [Tory] What's wrong with that?
- 'Cause I don't like rose petals--
- It's cute.
- Leading to your
stupid bedroom with the ceiling fan going.
It's like, this the same bedroom.
It's just like you
straightened out the comforter.
- [Announcer] To make the Valentine
in your life feel special
and avoid last minute hassle,
we have some ideas for you.
Discuss expectations with your partner.
Make a reservation if you plan to go out,
and enjoy the gift everyone
will fall in love with,
an auto-protection plan with CarShield.
CarShield protects its members
from the high cost of auto repairs.
Call 1-800-505-9619 for a free quote.
(groovy music)
- Well, you and Al always have something
to talk about in those cars.
- Yeah, we're chatty.
- Yeah, and I mean, I like
that you agree with me
that romance is embarrassing.
(hosts laughing)
Thank you.
- [Sam] I think romance is sexy.
- I just think men, I agree
with Al, it's cringe-worthy.
- [Sam] Really?
- To watch ourselves being romantic.
He's saying to watch it.
- It's weird to see.
- I'm gonna have a phone call
with Susan after this, that's his wife.
- Ooh!
- If you're leaving us right now,
you can still watch us live on Facebook.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] A cover story
controversy explodes.
When Esquire highlight
a Caucasian teen during
Black History Month.
Did they miss the mark or is
it much ado about nothing?
Then, food fight!
We'll tell you why country
star Miranda Lambert
dumped a perfectly good salad
right into a lady's lap.
And did someone call a doctor?
Dr. Drew Pinsky is back
and weighing in on the
day's trending topics
and news-making headlines.
More DBL is next.
(uplifting music)
(transitions to lively jazz music)
♪ Keep the feeling real ♪
♪ You know how I feel ♪
(audience cheering)
- [Narrator] Have you been
injured in an accident
because somebody wasn't paying
attention on the highway?
- When you've been injured
by a careless driver,
you have a lawyer.
- That's right.
When you need a lawyer, you have a lawyer.
No matter what kind of
accident you've been in,
call us at Saiontz and Kirk,
or go to YouHaveALawyer.com.
- [Announer] This President's Day,
Haverty's is honoring President Mom.
She made the executive decision
to buy store-bought
cookies for the bake sale.
She pardoned Emma for being Emma.
And then there was the
whole cone crisis thing.
President Mom, this President's
Day Sale is for you.
Everything is on sale.
Get big savings on sofas,
beds, dining sets, and more.
Now that's fiscally
responsible leadership.
Haverty's.
Life looks good.
- [Narrator] Dear suspicious
snackers, we get it.
We know it can be a texture thing,
and there are lots of
brands to choose from.
But it's time for you to
pick up your big spoon
and try new Hood Cottage Cheese.
It's the brand people have
trusted for more than 170 years.
A whole world of sweet
and savory combinations!
Like pineapple, cucumber and dill,
or classic country style.
And since it's packed
with satisfying protein,
you'll wanna try all of
Hood's amazing flavors.
Don't miss out on delicious.
New to your local dairy aisle.
(liveley music)
(transitions to emotional music)
(phone vibrates)
- Well, guys.
No school!
- [Kids] Snow day!
Yes!
- Come on!
- [Narrator] Otherwise
known as a WeatherTech day.
- Let's go.
- [Narrator] So, when
the weather turns bad,
you can still find a way to enjoy it.
With WeatherTech's laser
metric curve aligners,
seat protectors, and floor liners.
Order yours today at WeatherTech.com.
The ultimate protection for your vehicle.
(intense music)
- [Man] The Empire.