(upbeat music)
- More, you save more.
Up to $1,000 on furniture
that's already marked down.
With more styles and custom
fabrics to choose from.
Celebrate your independence
with furniture that fits you.
Havertys, life looks good.
- Right now at 11, numerous showers
and thunderstorms expected
on the 4th of July.
I'll have your hour-by-hour
forecast coming up.
(dramatic music)
- It is going to be a very
festive fourth here in D.C.
but I will tell you why some say
it is costing taxpayers too much money.
- [Narrator] And, if you
need even more of a reason
to stay sober behind
the wheel this holiday,
you have to see what a
suspected drunk driver
did to a police officer.
Your news starts now.
(dramatic music)
- [Sarah] We begin
tonight with a live look
at the National Mall.
Tomorrow, people will fill the Mall
to celebrate the 4th of July.
- [Shawn] It is all clear
tonight, but we are watching
for popup storms that could put a damper
on your holiday plans tomorrow.
- All right, let's get
right over to Caitlin now.
She is tracking when and where
the showers and storms could hit.
And you know, we're kinda used to this
on the 4th of July, aren't we?
- I know.
Yeah, we do this every year it feels like.
I mean, what's a holiday
without a weather challenge around here?
Especially in the summer.
We're gonna do that tomorrow.
Probably several rounds of
popup showers and storms.
Depending on where you are,
you might not see much.
In other spots, might see a lot.
So we're just gonna call
it a stormy day tomorrow,
because the potential is there
for lots of showers and
thunderstorms to fire up.
Some of which may be severe,
some of which may bring some heavy rains.
So that's a lot to keep track of
as you're trying to get
from your pool parties
to your barbecues, to
your firework festivities.
Storm Tracker Radar quiet tonight.
We got the day off, that felt great.
Showers and thunderstorms
last night were relentless.
So it was wonderful to not
see much around the Metro.
We're gonna stay quiet overnight tonight.
Just a few clouds,
muggy and mild, with that low of 76.
Looking ahead to tomorrow.
The heatwave rolls on.
It began on Tuesday, we're gonna continue
to see temperatures into the 90s.
And that heat index in the upper 90s.
But as early as the lunch hour,
showers and thunderstorms
are expected to fire up.
And we could be in for one of those days
where you're just dodging them.
So you might wanna have a backup plan
if you're gonna be outdoors, you know,
run inside as skies start to darken.
And there could a few postponements
out there tomorrow afternoon.
Here's your planning forecast warning.
No problem, temperatures
start out very mild,
around 80 degrees.
Near 90 by the lunch hour,
and then we'll be watching
for those showers and thunderstorms
in the fireworks time.
I think most of the heavy-hitting
action will be over with,
you know, the severe
weather, by nine o'clock.
But there could be some lingering rain.
We'll talk more about that
and I'll show you future casts
coming up in your full seven-day forecast.
Sarah and Shawn?
(upbeat band music)
- All right, now that
you know the forecast,
let's get ya caught up on
everything else you need to know
about some of the big events
in the District tomorrow.
Events in D.C. start just before noon
with the National Independence Day Parade
on Constitution Avenue Northwest.
Gates open at 3:30 p.m.
for President Trump's Salute to America.
That's at the Lincoln
Memorial which starts at 6:30.
And the annual Capitol
Fourth gets underway
on the West Lawn of the U.S. Capitol
at eight tomorrow night.
The big fireworks display
expected to begin after nine p.m.
Now, in addition to the
massive fireworks display
and the concert, new this year,
President Trump's Salute to America,
which include tanks, a military flyover,
and a hefty price tag that
some say is outrageous,
but others say is money well spent.
FOX 5's Josh Rosenthal is live
near the Lincoln Memorial
tonight with the latest.
Hey, Josh.
- Hey, Shawn, you know we
are less than 24 hours away
and as you can see, this
year's 4th of July's gonna be
a little different than years past.
It'll be more expensive, too;
however a whole lot of people
that I talked to out here
today said they think
it's money well spent.
- I think we spend a lot
of money on a lot of things
that we don't really
know where it's going,
so this is a great for, in my
mind, a great use of funds.
- If Congress doesn't get
their act together anyway
and wants to waste it on
their own pet projects,
why not have something to celebrate us?
- [Josh] But everyone
isn't quite so pleased.
Here's the deal: The
Washington Post reported
that the National Park
Service is diverting
about two and a half million
bucks in park entrance fees
to cover additional costs associated with
the President's event.
That money could have
been spent on improving
parks across the country
and even fixing potholes
on certain roads like the G.W. Parkway.
And remember, there's about
a 12 billion dollar backlog
of maintenance needs that the Park Service
is already struggling to handle.
- They claim that they
want to help protect
our national parks and
they want to provide
the money necessary and
to address the backlog
of the Park Service.
And then they turn around and they used
these very valuable
dollars from park visitors
to pay for this spectacle.
- Now, I did reach out to
the National Park Service
with a whole lot of questions about this,
but they didn't answer any of 'em.
Instead, they sent a
statement simply saying,
"The Department of the
Interior is committed to
"providing the American people a fantastic
"celebration of our nation's birthday.
"We are doing so consistent
with the Department's
"mission and historical practices."
I do wanna mention, we still don't have
a final total price tag
for this event tomorrow,
however, some of the stuff
that you're gonna see,
for instance, the extra
fireworks, have been donated.
Guys, back to you.
- And the President's
Salute to America tomorrow
is also expected to attract protestors.
Members of CODEPINK plan to demonstrate.
The group's organizers
said the event is turning
into a military style show of force
and does not represent the true meaning
of Independence Day.
They wanted to fly the Baby Trump balloon
we've seen flying in London
and other parts of Europe
as protest, but the National Park Service
denied their request.
CODEPINK says, "Even if
the balloon cannot fly,
"the group will take a stand."
- We do think it's important to oppose
what the President is doing.
I'm a D.C. resident, and
we know that the last time
President Trump wanted to
have a military parade,
the D.C. residents spoke out so forcefully
and our representatives
in the City Council
said, "No way."
- [Shawn] CODEPINK, again, wanted to fly
that Baby Trump balloon about
two feet off the ground,
but the Park Service grounded that idea.
- [Sarah] All right, here is a live look
at Reagan National Airport,
where this year's 4th of July
plans on the National Mall
will force the airport to
close down temporarily.
Flights will be suspended
from 6:15 to 7:45 p.m.,
for the military flyovers that are part of
the President's event.
And again from 9:00 to 9:45
p.m., for the fireworks.
Of course, you're encouraged to check with
your airline, see whether
or not your flight
may be affected by this.
TSA says, "Between today and Sunday,
"about 12 million people
will fly for the holiday."
- [Shawn] Virginia's
Department of Transportation
is sending drivers a serious
message on this holiday.
In a fun way, though.
This sign was spotted on I-95 today.
It reads, "You're not a firework.
"Don't drive lit."
In a nutshell, they're warning you not to
get behind the wheel if
you're under the influence.
- Rehearsals are wrapping up for
the 39th Annual A Capitol
Fourth celebration
hosted by John Stamos.
People will also get the
chance to see performances
by Sesame Street, Vanessa
Williams, the O'Jays,
and many others tomorrow.
The show starts at 8:00
p.m. on the West Lawn
of the Capitol Building.
- [Shawn] A little
pre-Independence Day celebration
this evening at FedExField.
SKYFOX gave us a bird's eye view
of tonight's Rolling Stones concert.
Mick Jagger, Keith Richards,
and the rest of the band
played in front of a packed house
for their No Filter Tour.
The legendary band delayed
the tour earlier this year
while Mick Jagger recovered
from heart surgery.
All right, well, there was
also an early fireworks show
just up the road at Six Flags in Largo.
It was part of the theme
park's July 4th Fest.
If you missed tonight's show, don't worry,
you'll have a chance to see it
several more times this week.
In fact, the next three
nights at Six Flags,
tonight's, or I should say
tomorrow night's display,
begins at 9:15.
There will also be
holiday celebrations all
over the region tomorrow,
and FOX 5 has you covered
from the easiest ways
to get around to where you
can find the local events
in your neighborhood.
It is all on the FOX 5 app.
(upbeat music)
- All right, a Maryland mother
is warning other parents after she said
her son contracted a flesh-eating bacteria
in Ocean City, Maryland.
- The images of her son's legs and arms
are difficult to look at.
FOX 5's Lindsay Watts is
here now with the story.
Lindsay, I understand
this isn't the only case
on the eastern seaboard.
- Shawn and Sarah, there have
been several of these lately.
In the case of a Florida
woman, it was deadly.
Now, fortunately, the boy
in Ocean City is recovering
despite these painful looking injuries.
This bacteria is rare,
but something to certainly
be aware of when you're swimming.
We wanna warn you, some
of the graphics here
are hard to watch.
These images have been
shared thousands of times
on social media, along
with a mother's message.
She says her son was in West Ocean City
swimming in the bay near Route 50.
She says a day later, she
noticed little spots on his body.
The next day, they were open wounds,
and then doctors informed her,
her son contracted Vibrio,
a flesh-eating bacteria.
Her latest update is good news.
Her son is healing.
But what happened comes just days
after a Florida woman died near Tampa.
Lynn Fleming's injuries are devastating.
And family says it all
started when the 77 year old
scraped her leg in the water.
- Told my mom multiple times,
I just wanna be normal again.
- [Lindsay] Elsewhere
in Florida, 12 year old
Kylei Parker had to have a
chunk of her leg removed.
It was after she went in the ocean
with a skateboard injury on her foot.
- [Michelle] Scuff on her toe, and--
- [Kylei] Which was almost healed.
- I mean, it almost cost her her life.
It's just so hard seeing
friends and family
and, you know, on the beach having fun,
'cause we were there doing the same thing.
- [Lindsay] The Centers
for Disease Control says
"The bacteria typically
enters the body through
"cuts, burns, or insect bites."
It is rare and the CDC
says, "Most who contract it
"have other health problems."
Early symptoms include
wet or swollen skin,
pain and fever.
Doctors say, "It's crucial to
get treatment immediately."
- A very small wound, and
the thing that terrifies you
as a doctor, is right in front of you,
you're seeing this get worse.
- Necrotizing fasciitis
is the medical term
for this condition.
The CDC says, "As many
as one in three people
"with the infection do
end up dying from it."
Sarah.
(people cheering)
(bell clanging)
- [Sarah] In case you missed
it, there were fireworks
on Wall Street ahead
of the 4th, literally.
The Dow, the NASDAQ, and
the S&P 500 all closing
at record highs.
The trading day ended with sparklers.
You see right there,
celebrating Macy's 4th of
July Fireworks Spectacular.
Markets will be closed
tomorrow for the holiday.
- All right, well, if
you had a little trouble
posting to social media today,
(upbeat music)
you weren't alone.
We're gonna tell you what
caused the world wide problems.
- Plus, caught on camera, a
man is accused of throwing
a lit firecracker at
a local police officer
sitting in a cruiser.
- [Shawn] And the blue crab
population is on the rise
in the Chesapeake Bay.
What it means for your
plate and also your wallet.
- [Sarah] And coming up on The Final 5,
the issue of adding a citizenship question
to the 2020 census seemed
like it was settled,
but then, the President tweeted
and now even members of his administration
are confused about what's going on.
Catch The Final 5 tonight at 11:30.
(upbeat rock music)
♪ You wanna make a fuss ♪
♪ Better listen up and listen good ♪
♪ You don't mess with America ♪
♪ You only get ♪
(upbeat rock music)
♪ You won't stop us ♪
- [Announcer] It's the final
lap of the Sheehy 8000.
Race in for special 4th
of July savings now.
Get up to 125% of KBB
value for your trade.
Plus, we're donating to the
American Heart Association.
♪ It's easy at Sheehy ♪
♪ Sheehy.com ♪
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Today,
people across the nation
are experiencing the benefits
of joining PenFed Credit Union.
With the PenFed car buying service,
they're finding the right
car at a better price.
And everyone is welcome to apply.
Join today at PenFed.org.
- [Announcer] The tools of a RE/MAX agent.
(drone buzzing)
The flying camera.
(camera clicks)
The mobile app.
(dog barks)
(phone chimes)
The automated alert.
The experience, the tools, the know-how.
That's the sign of a RE/MAX agent.
(engine revs)
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] This is
how driving should feel.
The Tech Advanced Nissan LEAF.
The best selling electric
vehicle of all time.
This is Nissan Intelligent Mobility.
- [Announcer] With the
PenFed car buying service
from PenFed Credit Union,
you can get rates as low as
2.49% APR on used vehicles.
And everyone is welcome to apply.
Visit PenFed.org.
♪ PenFed's got great rates for everyone ♪
- [Announcer] It's the final
lap of the Sheehy 8000.
Race in for special 4th
of July savings now.
Find your next vehicle
online with Easy Search.
Plus, we're donating to the
American Heart Association.
♪ It's easy at Sheehy ♪
♪ Sheehy.com ♪
- [Announcer] Get a drain
cleaning for only 99 dollars.
♪ Michael & Son ♪
(upbeat trumpet music)
- A Navy Seal court-martialed
for the murder of a teenage ISIS militant
has been found not guilty.
- This year's event
will be unlike anything
we've ever seen before.
- In the end, the U.S. prevailing
two to one over England.
- [Weatherman] 91 for your 4th of July.
- [Reporter] A total solar eclipse
seen across South America today.
It's the world's first in two years.
(upbeat electronic music)
- [Sarah] All right, here's a look at some
of the top stories
we're following tonight.
Another legal setback for
President Trump's effort
to build his border wall.
Today, a Federal Appeals Court ruled
the Federal Government cannot tap into
Defense Department money to
build sections of the wall
in Arizona and New Mexico.
The Appeals Court ruling
upheld a lower court decision.
It is unclear, though, if
the Trump Administration
will appeal.
Frightening moments for
a Prince George's County
police officer.
A man is accused of throwing
a lit firework at an officer
inside a marked cruiser
Saturday in Forestville.
Investigators determined
the incident was preplanned
because someone recorded
it on their phone.
Fortunately, the officer was not hurt.
Police have identified
a person of interest.
The driver of a car died
on the scene of a crash
with a truck in Montgomery County.
Happened around three p.m. in Poolesville
at River Road, at Old River Road.
The crash caused a utility
pole to snap in half.
Also took down some power lines.
There is no word tonight
what caused that crash.
- Funeral services were held today for
the retired NYPD detective
who fought to make sure
that 9/11 first responders
are never forgotten.
53 year old Luis Alvarez
died last Saturday
after a battle with colorectal cancer.
He attributed his illness to months
of digging through rubble at Ground Zero
following the September
11 terrorist attacks.
Today he was remembered as
a brave and faithful man.
- At the end of the
day, and all throughout
his remarkable life, Lu just
wanted to do what's right.
And he desperately wanted others,
particularly those in
positions of great power,
to follow suit.
- [Shawn] In June, Alvarez
and TV host John Stewart
got very emotional when they
testified before Congress,
hoping to convince
lawmakers to pass a bill
that would continue funding
the 9/11 Victim Compensation Fund.
- The Maryland Department of Health
is reporting its first heat related death
of the year in the state.
The victim was an elderly
woman in Anne Arundel County.
The Department, of course, has some tips
to stay cool out there.
"Drink lots of fluids.
"Wear loose-fitting and
light-colored clothing.
"Also, avoid the direct sunlight,
"and take it easy with
the outdoor activity.
Just a reminder for you.
- [Shawn] All right, got
a little good news now
for crab lovers.
A new report revealed the Chesapeake Bay
blue crab population is
up 60% from last year.
That's the highest since 2012.
But the people who run
the Bethesda Crab House
told us, "The growing crab population
"won't likely translate to lower prices
"for you crab lovers."
- Population increase isn't that much
of a population increase when it comes to
price becoming less, you know.
There are more of 'em,
but not more of a lot.
More of a little.
- [Shawn] Experts say,
"It takes several years
"of population increases before there is
"a change in price."
(bright Caribbean music)
- Now from the Bay to a story
from under the sea.
There's a new little mermaid in town.
Halle Bailey, half of the
sister duo Chloe and Halle,
will be starring as Ariel
in Disney's live-action
remake of The Little Mermaid.
The film's director released
a statement saying that
Halle possesses a rare
combination of spirit, heart,
youth, innocence, and substance.
Production for the
live-action Little Mermaid
begins in 2020.
- [Shawn] That's awesome.
- [Sarah] Yeah, all right, all right.
- [Shawn] Halle Berry for a minute.
(Sarah laughs)
- No, no, Bailey.
- Bailey.
- She's a singer.
- A little different.
- All right.
What a beautiful Wednesday.
Time-lapse video from the
Friendship Heights neighborhood
in northwest D.C. this evening.
- [Shawn] Yeah, our
photojournalist, Van Applegate,
shot this, but there's a
chance we will not have
this picturesque scene
tomorrow, right, Caitlin?
- [Caitlin] Yeah, I'm
hoping we could least clear
things out by fireworks time.
It's gonna be a, kind of a busy afternoon
with showers and thunderstorms,
so you're dodging around that.
Peak time probably about
10 to, or 12 to six.
- So a little bit earlier
means let's try to get this
wrapped up.
- All right, yes.
- [Caitlin] At least in my mind. (laughs)
There's some red, white, and blue for ya.
- [Sarah] All right, look at that.
The Capitol Wheel all lit up tonight.
- [Shawn] Beautiful!
- That wheel puts on a
show night after night
and we love to display it for ya.
Beautiful evening out there.
It's warm, but it's clear.
Storms stayed away from the Metro today.
In fact, we barely even got anything
anywhere close by.
It was nice to have a night off from that
despite the fact that it was
another hot and humid day.
So, it's all red, white, and
blue as you go into tomorrow.
Can't let the weather stop you.
Just gotta be inside.
Maybe if, you know,
you're out by the pool,
out doing some barbecuing and those skies
start to darken and the rain comes down.
So, today, like we said, was gorgeous.
Fourth of July eve, so hopefully everyone
is in full festivity mode.
Beautiful sunset captured
by our friend Will
here on Twitter.
This is in Olney, you
see the last of that sun
slipping below the horizon.
A lot of beautiful
yellow and orange color.
That looks like a hot summer sunset to me.
And, in fact, it was a hot summer day.
93 was the magic number for
Reagan, Dulles, and BWI.
It was hot out there.
It was above normal.
It was also humid.
And those heat index values
were getting close to,
and in some places surpassing,
the century mark earlier this afternoon.
83 degrees in the District right now.
Winds are still out of the northwest.
That's what saved us today.
That wind from the north
prevented any storms
from really initiating,
and so we were quiet
and we'll be quiet again
into the overnight.
83 outside right now here
in the District, still warm.
84 in Annapolis.
We've fallen back into the
upper 70s north and west.
77 in Frederick, 78 in Dulles.
So, national radar shows that there were
some showers and storms
over the past three hours
across the mountains.
Just really didn't get anything local.
Tomorrow's a different story.
We actually have a bit of
a system coming through.
So that will really tap
into the heat and humidity
and initiate some storms.
9:00 nothing, but it
will be a quick change
to the noon hour, getting
started early on these storms
where we do expect some showers
and thunderstorms to bubble up.
Look at this; that's a lotta coverage.
While they are widely
scattered, it looks like
a safe bet everyone's gonna see some rain,
at least at some point.
And areas towards our
west really look favored.
Here's 5:00 across the I-81
down to the I-64 Corridor.
We are talking about some
heavy rain potential there.
Notice by 9:00, most
of this has faded away.
So, while you might have
some wet grounds out there
as you're setting up your lawn chairs
to watch the fireworks, we might be okay
if we get this all over
with early, hopefully.
Into Friday we go, and it's
gonna be the same type of thing.
Starting out hazy, late day
showers and thunderstorms fire.
We are still just in that pattern.
Nothing's changing.
Marginal risk of severe
weather, which means
a severe threat isn't too high.
Nothing widespread,
maybe some damaging winds
here and there, but I do think
we have to keep an eye on
the heavy rain threat
and the potential for
maybe some flooding if we
keep getting these storms
one after another tomorrow.
So 92 degrees for that high temperature,
scattered showers and
storms on the 4th, sorry.
Just the way it is this
year, and you know what?
It's just the way it's gonna stay through
the rest of the holiday weekend.
So, we're not shaking this pattern yet.
Hot, humid, and stormy.
Until next week, but I
will tell you, when we get
to next week, the weather
looks much improved.
Warmer or dryer, still nice and warm,
but seasonably so with less humidity.
It looks good Monday,
Tuesday, and Wednesday.
And that's your seven
day, have a great 4th.
Shawn, over to you.
- President Trump put his feud with
the U.S. Women's Soccer
team on hold, sort of.
The White House said
today, it will send members
of the Trump Administration to France
for the final game on Sunday.
Of course, the U.S. facing
off against the Netherlands.
Last week, the President ranted on Twitter
about midfielder Megan Rapinoe.
Months ago, she said she wouldn't go
to the White House even if the team won.
She also refused to sing
along with the National Anthem
during the World Cup
to show her opposition
to the Trump Administration.
(upbeat music)
Just a reminder, Sunday
is the World Cup Final.
Defending champs, Team USA,
will take on the Netherlands.
You can watch it live on FOX
5 right here Sunday at 11 a.m.
- Well, it was all about
the burgers at Z-Burger
in Tenleytown today.
The restaurant holding its 10th Annual
Independence Day Burger
Eating Championship.
15 contestants had 10 minutes to eat
as many burgers as possible.
The winner, Molly Skyler,
ate 32 and walked away
with the $1500 prize.
This is the 5th time she's won that event.
- [Shawn] And we held our very own
FOX 5 Z-Burger Eating
Contest tonight at 10 p.m.
David Brunelli, one of the
top ranked competitive eaters
in the world, that's him, right there,
scarfing 'em down.
- Wow.
- [Shawn] He dominated tonight here too.
He beat out our FOX 5 staffers
who gave it their all.
A big shout out tonight
to Justin, Lindsay,
Brandon, and Coop.
They gave it their best.
- I love how Lindsay was
so dainty.
- She was something.
- [Sarah] She was chewing
and covering her mouth,
something you would not see
in the burger eating championship.
- [Shawn] No, everybody else
was just chuggin' 'em down.
She got about a fourth of a burger in.
(Sarah laughs)
I think the champ
got two and a half.
I think Justin got like--
- It's hard.
- Almost all of it
- It's tough, like, there's
a lot of bread involved with that.
I don't know how they do it.
- It's just a lot of--
- I really don't.
- It's a lot, I was--
- Look at you.
- Cheering her on.
We called her the silent assassin.
- You were cheering her on?
- I was trying to cheer.
Yeah, I was like, "You've got this, girl.
"Let's go, let's go, let's go."
- [Sarah] Okay, was that what
you were saying?
- Yeah.
- Or was it, "Eat more, eat more."
(Shawn laughs)
Like a drill sergeant,
there, Shawn, my gosh.
- I was trying, you know--
- Poor Lindsay. (laughs)
- Coach.
You gotta, I was rootin' for her.
I wanted her to win.
Girl power.
- Take one for the team, guys.
Thanks for doin' that.
- All right.
And, comin' up,
(upbeat music)
seems like a no-brainer.
People should know to practice
safety behind the wheel.
- We're gonna show you
the video of a crash
that landed a suspected
drunk driver in handcuffs
and behind bars.
That's next.
(upbeat music)
♪ What about your friends ♪
♪ Are they standin' round ♪
♪ Will they let you down ♪
- Hey, did you hear
the big news?
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Huge Koons
July 4th savings are here
on thousands of new Koons
Toyotas, Fords, Chevys,
Jeeps, and more.
- [Group] Our biggest
July 4th savings ever.
- [Announcer] Get started
now online at Koons.com.
- But wait, there's more.
(thunder crackles)
(gentle music)
♪ Make yourself comfortable, ooh ♪
♪ Make yourself comfortable, baby ♪
- [Announcer] This is not a bed.
It's a revolution in sleep.
(electronic music)
The Sleep Number 360 Smart Bed
is on sale now during our
lowest prices of the season.
(upbeat music)
It senses your movement
and automatically adjusts to
keep you both comfortable.
(snoring)
It even helps with this.
So you wake up ready to
hit the ground running.
Don't miss our 4th of July special
with a queen Sleep Number
360 c4 Smart Bed now $1299
plus free premium delivery
when you add a base.
Ends Sunday.
Sleep Number, proven quality sleep.
- [Announcer] It's the final days of our
4th of July sales event,
your last chance to get
great deals on our Ford SUV lineup.
Now get 0% financing for
72 months on Ford Explorer.
Or 0% for 60 months on
Escape, Edge, and Expedition.
It's no wonder Ford SUVs have the highest
brand loyalty in the industry.
Now, during the final
days, get 0% financing
for 72 months on Explorer.
Get zero for 60 on Escape,
Edge, and Expedition.
Or choose $7,800 in total
savings on Ford Explorer.
(knocking)
- Hey, you still there?
(upbeat music)
There's more.
- [Announcer] On top
of huge Koons July 4th
savings on thousands
of new Koons vehicles,
you'll get up to thousands
more for your trade.
If your car's worth 8000,
- [Group] Koons will give you 10.
- [Announcer] Get started
now online at Koons.com.
(triumphant news music)
- Okay, so ahead of holiday festivities,
here is a reminder not to drink and drive.
A police officer in Ohio
was driving down a road
when another vehicle appeared,
but it was going the wrong way.
Police say the driver of that vehicle was
under the influence.
The officer turned on emergency lights,
but that did not stop
the driver from slamming
into the officer's patrol car.
Thankfully, no one was
injured, but the driver was,
of course, arrested and
faces several charges.
- All right, you might wanna
be careful with your cell phone
as you celebrate this holiday.
Tech company Asurion
says the 4th of July is
the most dangerous time for your phone.
It found phone damage
incidents jumped by about 60%
around Independence Day.
Cracked screens increased by 40%.
Misplaced phones jumped more than 75%.
The worst culprit, water damage.
That goes up nearly 250%
during the holiday weekend.
- Keep them away from your pool.
All right, if you've been
having trouble with some of your
social media accounts
today, you're not alone.
People around the world
began reporting issues today
with some of the apps on their phones,
specifically Facebook,
Instagram, Twitter, and Whatsapp.
Users reported bugs, such
as images not loading
on Instagram, and problems
with Twitter Direct messages,
including the app
showing notifications for
unread Direct messages that were not there
when users checked their inbox.
It was so frustrating all day today.
How did we live without it? (laughs)
- I don't know, I'm sorry.
I had to, you know, talk
to somebody about it.
- All right, up next, one final check
of your holiday forecast.
(upbeat music)
- We'll be right back.
(electric guitar music)
(gentle music)
(engine revs)
- [Announcer] This is
how driving should feel.
The Tech Advanced Nissan LEAF.
The best selling electric
vehicle of all time.
This is Nissan Intelligent Mobility.
- [Announcer] Mychoice, the nation's
premiere casino loyalty program,
is now at Hollywood Casino
at Charles Town Races
in West Virginia, so you can play local,
or at over 35 amazing
mychoice destinations
across the country.
And earn rewards like trips
to thrilling Las Vegas,
or a Mercedes Benz lease.
Start earning today.
New members sign up for
a mychoice Rewards Card
and get rolling with up to $500 on us.
At Hollywood Casino at Charles Town Races.
All gaming is regulated by
the West Virginia Lottery.
(exciting music)
- [Announcer] Come see what's new
this summer at Busch Gardens
and WaterCountry USA.
Soar 80 feet high on the
new Finnegan's Flyer.
(screaming)
Then blast off on
the new Cutback Water Coaster.
And experience a whole
different park after dark
at Busch Gardens Summer Nights.
Enjoy your favorite thrills into the night
with new entertainment each week.
Featuring stars from America's Got Talent.
Right now, save up to 50% on tickets.
Busch Gardens and WaterCountry USA.
- [Announcer] It's the final days
of our 4th of July sales event.
Don't miss your last chance
for huge deals on F-series,
America's best selling
trucks for 42 years straight.
Get 0% APR financing for 72
months on the Ford F-150.
Or check out the all new 2019 Ford Ranger
and see why it's the
ultimate adventure gear.
During final days, get 0%
for 72 months on Ford F-150.
And if you've ever served in the military
or are a first responder, get 1500 more
in appreciation cash on these Ford trucks
on top of all offers.
- A groom's first look
at his bride before their wedding
turned out to be a big prank.
Take a look.
(people laughing)
All right, so the groom
actually turned to see
his veiled bride, was
actually his little brother.
His brother's a U.S. Army Sergeant.
Took leave from his post in Germany
to fulfill his duties as the best man.
The groom was stunned to
see his younger brother
standing there in their
mother's wedding gown.
- That's really cute.
- Yeah, it was.
- [Caitlin] You know, what a
surprise but also hilarious.
- [Sarah] I love how
he couldn't even really
fit into the wedding
gown either, by the way.
- Nice of mom to let him put it on.
I would have been like, "No, dude, you're
"not wearing my wedding dress."
Yeah, you can forget that.
- All right.
- Not my son.
- That's pretty good.
- Right.
- Jim Lokay's up next with The Final 5.
- [Shawn] Have a great night.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Summer
has never been so green
when you go with Toyota,
and go with a Prius,
the hybrid that started it all.
Now, with more fuel efficient
models to choose from,
including Prime, the original liftback.
And now an available all-wheel drive model
to handle tougher weather conditions.
For a limited time, get a
Prius with 1000 cashback
from Toyota.
Be sure to visit
buyatoyota.com for more offers.
Toyota, let's go places.
- [Announcer] The Hyundai 4th
of July sales event is on.
Featuring 16 award winning
Hyundai sedans and SUVs.
And they're all on sale.
Now, lease an Elantra
for only 179 a month.
Or buy with 0% APR for 60 months.
Hurry in today.
- [Announcer] This fall,
(upbeat music)
a star-studded comedy
about a family that's broke
(horn honks)
but not broken.
- I'll have a 12-biscuit biscuit bonanza.
- Oh, get me some cheese grits.
- I will have biscuits and gravy with--
- A side of type-2 diabetes?
- [Announcer] Bless the Harts
coming this fall to FOX.
- Coming up tonight on The Final 5,
with one tweet, the President
turns an issue that
everyone thought was settled
into total--