- [Narrator] Right now at
11, tracking the storm.
From the FOX 5 Weather App to Facebook.
- We are tracking another system.
- [Narrator] We're taking you step by step
through this winter storm,
approaching in just hours.
- Our team coverage continues
with preparations for the storm.
Why some road crews are actually
encouraged by Sue's forecast.
(dramatic tone)
- [Narrator] Plus, a bathroom debate
and a fight for student rights goes viral.
How Virginia ended up back
in the national spotlight.
Your news starts now.
(dramatic music)
- We're gonna begin tonight with a winter
weather watch for much of the DC region.
Snow, sleet and freezing
rain are all on the menu
and this winter mix could be nasty,
especially during the morning commute.
- It's prompted just about
every school district
here to cancel class tomorrow along with
the federal government.
All of those closures
are listed, of course,
at the bottom of your screen.
For now though, let's
get right to Sue Palka
for a breakdown of when the first flakes
will start falling.
Sue?
- Hi there, Sarah.
I think it's gonna be anytime between
about four and six in
the morning here around
the Beltway and yeah, it's morning snow
and a messy, icy mix tomorrow afternoon.
Unfortunately, this does not stay all snow
which would be the better scenario.
It's easier to get rid of.
Ice causes so many problems.
But it does look like we are going
to see that changeover.
As we start with snow that
we now see showing up,
especially south of Interstate 64,
that will continue to spread
from southwest to northeast over our area
and by the time you wake
up tomorrow morning,
by sunrise, I think you
will see snow outside.
This is all starting to push up.
Now, we do not expect much accumulation
for southern Virginia.
They'll start with a little bit.
It will quickly changeover down there.
But quite a sprawling system all the way
up to the plains, across
St. Louis to Cincinnati
and now here into the
mid-Atlantic and we will be
dealing with it for many hours tomorrow.
We did have to take our
snow totals down a little
bit today based on the
model output and the
faster changeover to
sleet and freezing rain.
We're still gonna go with
the three to five inches.
It could be closer to
the three inches though
with snow because the
changeover now appears as
though it'll be sometime
in the late morning.
Out here, the changeover's a little later.
We could get a rate of
snow one inch per hour
for a few hours in the morning
and that's where you'll get your pile up,
but unfortunately for all of our area,
this may end, especially in
the northern and western suburbs.
Everybody west of 95 has to watch for
the potential for significant icing as
the temperature begins to,
the temperature a lot begins to rise
and changes that snow over
to that combination of
sleet and freezing rain.
Could a quarter inch of ice be possible
in some of these areas?
We think that is.
And that may occur early in the afternoon
and continue until about the time
of the evening rush hour.
So, we wrap it up with a
quick look at your planner.
8 am, 30 degrees, it's snowing.
By the noon hour, we're at 32.
We're mixing across much of the area.
Maybe northern Maryland not quite yet,
or western Maryland.
By four o'clock, it should be raining
here at DC, but possibly, still freezing
rain in our far Northern
and Western suburbs.
Much more to come,
including our hour by hour
feature cast just ahead.
Sarah.
- [Sarah] Well, crews have already
hit the roads, laying
sand, salt and brine.
Now, they are literally standing by
waiting for the wallop
so they can get to work
on thousands of miles of roadway.
Our team coverage of this approaching
winter storm continues.
FOX 5's Lauren DeMarco joins us
from Fairfax now with the
very latest out there.
Lauren.
- Sarah, it's incredible
to watch these guys
do their work, filling
up truck after truck
with salt and sand.
They are heading out to the interstates
from this saltdom in Fairfax, and they are
asking for help from the public tomorrow,
when all of this wet
stuff starts coming down.
- If everybody stays home, hang out,
watch the Channel Five,
it would be great for us.
- Stay home, stay home, stay home.
- As it's gonna be pretty nasty throughout
the day tomorrow and into
tomorrow night's rush
so we're really asking the folks
to stay off the roads if at all possible.
- [Sarah] A unified
message from transportation
and highway officials in Virginia,
Maryland and the district.
- For folks who do venture out,
I don't know why they would do that,
we want them to obviously fall behind
our snow plows.
- [Sarah] Thousands of
plows and salt trucks
are being deployed across the region,
loading up and getting
in place over night.
Preparations actually began over
the last few days, with crews pre-treating
highways, local roads
and known trouble spots
with liquid brine, and officials are
encouraged by the forecast.
- It's gonna be coming in as snow from
what we're hearing, which is beautiful
in terms of interacting with the brine,
and we're gonna have 3,000 trucks out,
starting overnight to
be able to push the snow
out of the way, as you see,
they're starting to roll through here.
- [Sarah] Anyone who has to be out,
is urged to prepare with
an emergency supply kit,
charged cell phone and full tank of gas.
Plenty of people heading that advice
at Costco's popular gas station
on Westox Road in Fairfax.
- It's crazy, it's always busy here,
but today's extremely busy.
People think that the sky is gonna fall.
- I think people don't wanna get stuck.
- [Sarah] Over at Home
Depot, people stocking up
on ice melt, shovels and
other usual necessities.
- What I'm concerned about is how much
snow we're gonna get.
- I have three boys, so
they're gonna be working.
- So, between snow, freezing rain,
or at least freezing precipitation,
and then possibly some
ice, this is expected
to impact the next three rush hours.
Vedot told me tonight that because this is
starting with snow and it's expecting
to accumulate, they will
be in the sub-divisions
as well, and they and all of the area
officials are asking that,
in your neighborhood,
try to park in a driveway
or all on one side
of the road, that way the plows
have an easier time getting by.
Back to you in the studio.
- Several area schools are already out
of snow days, in fact, tomorrow's storm
will send more schools over their days
budgeted for weather cancellations.
Montgomery Country used its
two make up days already.
Howard County used its four make up days,
if they have to miss any more,
the school district will have to appeal
to the State Board of Education
and ask for forgiveness,
or make adjustments
to the school calendar.
Fairfax, Prince William, Loudoun
and Anne Arundel County Schools
all have days to spare.
- [Sarah] The storm is
forcing Metro to adjust
bus and rail service.
Trains will run every 12 minutes in
the morning to allow workers
to de-ice the tracks.
The schedule could change as the weather
unfolds during the day.
Metro Bus will operate under
severe snow service plans.
So, that means buses will provide
limited service on major roadways only,
and Metro access will only provide
return trips home for customers
between four a.m. and seven p.m.
All other trips will be canceled.
And remember, you can
track the weather 24/7
on the FOX 5 Weather app.
You can also get the
latest on FOX 5 Morning,
beginning at 4 a.m.
(intense music)
- Another life lost on
what is being called
the highway of death.
Juan Castillo was killed last night
on Indian Head Highway route 210
in Acookeek, Maryland.
Now, the circumstances around
the crash that killed Kim,
are similar to a crash
that killed three children
on that same road back in December.
FOX 5's Lindsay Watts spoke with
Castillo's heartbroken family.
Lindsay.
- Shunning that crash last night
and the one in December,
drivers were stopped
at a red light here on Indian Head Highway
when another vehicle came barreling up
from behind and crashed into their car.
We have told you about all of the efforts
to make Indian Head Highway safer,
but police say it also falls on drivers
to pay attention when
they're behind the wheel.
(speaking in foreign language)
I feel he's my daddy.
I love him so much and I'm gonna miss him.
- [Lindsay] One minute as Castillo
was a father and grandfather.
He was driving with a
family member Monday night
about six miles from his home in Waldorph.
- My brother-in-law is driving the car.
- [Sarah] This is what
happened to that vehicle,
a Ford Escape.
According to police, it was stopped
at a red light on Indian Head Highway
on Barry Road in Accokeek.
Investigators say a
female driver didn't stop,
plowing in to the Escape.
Menedez Castillo died at the hospital.
Although his family had only recently
moved here from Virginia,
they were all well aware
of 210's notoriety.
Menedez Castillo saw news coverage
of the horrifying crash that claimed
the life of three children.
- When I saw that accident pass
on December, he say, oh my God,
everybody has to be careful,
that street is danger.
- [Lindsay] Prince George's County Police
have ramped up enforcement on the highway,
issuing 3,700 citations in just
the last months and a half.
There was a DUY checkpoint
earlier this month.
The county is working to get state funding
to improve the road, and a bill advancing
in Indianapolis would add up to seven
roving speed cameras.
Right now, there is only one permanent
speed camera on 210.
- I think they're doing
everything I can think of.
- [Lindsay] The road is such a hazard,
there's a community group devoted
to making it safer.
Ron Weiss is part of that.
- When we think of 210 as our main street,
and it's just not a good feeling
when you go out on your main street
and worry about being killed.
- [Lindsay] He says these
recent fatal crashes
have been preventable,
and it's up to drivers
to take back control.
Back here live now, the crash last night
is still under investigation.
Police are trying to find out why
that female driver didn't stop.
Back to you.
(intense music)
- [Sarah] New at 11 now, Virginia House
Democrats today said they are treating
the sexual assault allegations against
Lieutenant Governor
Justin Fairfax seriously.
In a statement they said, we respect all
survivors and believe they
should be fully heard.
In response, the attorney for accuser,
Meredith Watson said, apparently,
the Virginia House Democratic Caucus
believes that courageous victims of rape
need to be heard, just not by them.
Miss Watson is counting
on the General Assembly
to do the right thing
and hold hearings now.
- [Sarah] The gunman who shot up a car
outside a popular ice
arena in the district
is still on the run tonight.
The shooting happened this afternoon
near the Fort Dupont Ice
Arena in the Southeast.
The gunman shot two men and a child,
one man is critical, the other two
are expected to be okay.
Tonight, police are looking
for a silver Hyundai
that might be connected to the shooting.
- Good news for Southeast DC families
who rely on the Fort Dupont Ice Arena,
the city's only full-size, public,
indoor ice rink, will get
a much needed facelift
thanks to a deal reached
between Mayor Bowser
and the friends of Fort Dupont ice arena,
the non-profit that runs that rink.
If the group raises three million
of the $30 million expansion budget
by next February, the city will sign
the contract to start the project.
The expansion will create
a new two-rink arena.
- [Announcer] Well, from the ice
to the ball field, the
Washington Nationals had
their first squad spring
training workout today.
The Nets play their first practice game
in four days in West Palm Beach, Florida.
Looks like the weather's
a lot nicer there.
By the way, Net superstar Bryce Harper
is not on the field, he's
a free agent right now
and still has not signed with the team.
- Some Montgomery County High School
students have been
encouraging other students
to use a racial slur and, of course,
it's stirring some controversy.
- Evan Lambert is working
on that story tonight.
Evan.
- Sian, parents and
school leaders met tonight
to talk about solutions to what
the principal called, a racist act.
More coming up.
- Each of us have gifts that express
themselves in different ways.
- [Sarah] Former President Obama
is heading up an alliance to
support young men of color.
We'll take you to Oakland for the first
My Brothers Keeper summit.
And, coming up tonight on The Final 5,
Bernie Sanders is back for another
Democratic Primary, so what does this
announcement mean for
the presidential race,
and what will be different
from his 2016 campaign?
Catch The Final 5 tonight at 11:30.
("Coldest Winter" by Kanye West)
♪ Goodbye my friend ♪
♪ Will I ever love ♪
- [Announcer] Wendy Wednesday.
Our hot talk all-stars
lay it all on the table.
Plus, Dina Lohan is here.
Tomorrow at 11 on FOX 5.
- [Announcer] Your Ford Dealers
Presidents Day sales
event was just extended
through February 28th.
Save on America's best selling trucks
for 42 years straight, with 0%
for 72 months, plus
1500 bonus cash on F150.
That's right, we're making it easier
than ever to get in to any new Ford.
But don't wait because
these Presidents Day
offers end February 28th.
Hurry to your local Ford
dealer for best selection.
It's your last change for zero for 72,
plus 1500 bonus cash, or choose 11,350
total savings on select F150's.
- [Announcer] The Hyundai Presidents Sales
event is going on now.
Get huge savings on our full
line-up of cars and SUVs.
Hyundai is also making
some history of its own.
The Hyundai Kona has been named the 2019
North American Utility
Vehicle of the Year.
Incredible vehicles, monumental savings.
Find yours during the
Hyundai Presidents Day
sales event, going on now.
Get a Santa Fe for zero percent APR,
plus 500 bonus cash.
Or 3,000 cash back.
Now extended an extra 500 for Government
employees affected by the shut down.
- Show me The Crown.
Show me Homecoming.
Baby's last videos on YouTube.
- Amy, do you mind giving
someone else a turn?
- Oh, yeah, I've made myself
a little comfortable here.
- I got a pizza for Amy.
- Yes, that's me.
- [Announcer] Xfinity
lets you search Netflix,
Prime Video and YouTube with
the sound of your voice.
- And I don't have my wallet, so.
- [Announcer] It's simple, easy, awesome.
Switch to Xfinity and get
started with this great offer.
Plus, ask about 4K Ultra HD
and packages that include Netflix.
Click, call or visit a store today.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Choose to go
out in style this winter.
Choose the Versatile XT5.
Current NGM owners and lessons
get this low mileage lease on this 2019
Cadillac XT5 from 439 per month.
- [Announcer] Fourth of
July has its fireworks.
Christmas, gifts.
But what about Presidents Day.
Let's just say, the
voters will be very happy.
Announcing our best offers on America's
best selling brand.
You gotta love democracy.
Through February 28th
only, get four thousand
total cash on select Ford SUVs.
Hurry to your local Ford dealers for best
selection during the
Presidents Day sales event.
- Today on FOX 5 Morning, we talked
to the first ever woman
police chief in Fairfax City.
- Plus, Maryland and Virginia suing
the president over the national emergency.
- Then tomorrow, expect school delays
and closings with the
upcoming winter storm.
- We'll keep you updated with our team
coverage and weather
and traffic on the 5's.
- Tomorrow on FOX 5 Morning.
- Students at a Montgomery
County High School
have been encouraging other
students to use a racial slur.
Some students have actually been sharing
a card that gives other students a pass
to use the N word.
Tonight, administrators and parents met
to talk about solutions.
FOX's Evan Lambert is
here now with the latest.
Evan.
Sian, school officials found the passes
on February 8th at Winston Church Hill
High School in Patomac, Maryland.
Tonight, concerned parents and students
wanted to hear what the schools plan was
to discourage racist language and acts.
This is what the passes looked like.
They're based on a meme of a Willy
Wonka Golden Ticket.
The holder, according to the ticket,
gets permission to use the N word.
Tonight, school officials said they have
come up with a plan to
be rolled out in phases
to turn the episode
into a teachable moment.
Students would be educated
about racism and equality.
A group of about 40 student leaders
have already met about how they can talk
to other students.
Many parents thought using the students
own voices to educate each other
would be most effective.
- I mean, we all came here thinking that
there was a plan in play, and there is
a lot of brain-storming going on,
which is good, but at the end of the day,
I think that it's gonna
take way more than that.
Peer pressure is huge in high school,
and if we can use that for good,
and have them influence their peers
and say, just because
you hear it in a song,
that doesn't mean it's okay.
- It starts with the kids,
it starts with the parents,
it starts with the school, the teachers,
everybody collectively play a role
and making a change.
- Back when the passes were discovered,
principal Brandis Hecor
called the incident, quote,
a racist, hateful act that does not
reflect the values of Churchill students.
The students involved
have been disciplined
in accordance with the code of conduct.
Sarah.
- Jussie Smolletts
lawyers insist The Empire
actor did not orchestrate assault,
despite speculation that he paid two men
to attack him on a Chicago street.
The two brothers, who
were initially questioned
and released, reportedly
told police Smollett
paid them to rehearse and
carry out the assault.
They also said Smollett was
upset there was not enough
attention being paid to a threatening
letter he had received.
The FBI has joined a
separate investigation
in to that letter, and
investigators believe
Smollett may have sent
that letter to himself.
- A Virginia school
district is now considering
a new proposal to allow
transgender students
to use the restroom of their choice.
Dozens of people turned
out for a school board
hearing in Gloucester County tonight
to discuss the plan.
It would allow transgender students
to use the restroom of choice,
as long as they assert their new gender
identity for at least six months.
The proposal would reverse
the county's current policy
that's been a subject of a lawsuit
since it was adopted back in 2014.
That proposal said students could only use
the restroom that corresponded
with their sex at birth.
- [Sarah] It almost
looks like the real deal,
but it's not.
Fake money, mainly one
hundred dollar bills,
is making its way around
Northern Virginia.
But there are some easy ways to spot
the counterfeit bills and
avoid becoming a victim
or to avoid passing it along.
- [Narrator] You can see
on this counterfeit bill
it says for motion picture use only.
A lot of the security
features aren't there.
When we compare to this
legitimate $100 bill,
you can see the difference in color,
there's a different feel on the texture.
- [Sarah] The Stafford
County Sheriff's Office
there saying they have no
idea right now how many
fake bills are in circulation in the area.
- All right, well we will have some snow,
and maybe some sleet, rain, ice,
and circulation in our area tomorrow.
- There's our forecast.
(laughs)
- Thank you, Sian.
- Good night, everyone.
It's been a long day.
- You wish, stay.
(laughs)
- Well, I've gotta show you how close
it's getting, and fortunately for us,
we get to get home before this starts,
but if you have a
morning commute tomorrow,
and I know a lot of schools have canceled,
the government has
canceled, I'm glad about it
because the snow could be falling
very intensely, so
visibility is a problem.
And, while the roads have
been brined and treated,
if we do get a burst of some moderate
to heavy snow that falls at a rate
of an inch per hour, even
for three or four hours,
that could be a real problem.
And, temperatures are
going to continue to drop,
we're at 38 degrees, so there will be
stickage tomorrow morning.
It's not the coldest night, so that means
this will be, somewhat, slushy, wet snow
as it falls, heavy wet
snow, and we'll see this
primarily in the morning hours,
and then the changeover
late morning to noon.
That timing of the changeover
is going to be crucial,
but overnight temperatures
near 30 to about 32 degrees.
Here's our storm tracker radar,
and you can see that we do see snow
trying to expand, certainly
aloft, north of 64 now.
Is it hitting the ground down there?
Probably not just yet,
we've got some dry air
to overcome briefly, but you can see
that is all making steady
progress south west to north east.
And we still expect it in here
between about six to seven in the morning,
crossing the beltway.
Big storm, as you know,
it has had an impact
for Nebraska, for Kansas, for Oklahoma,
for St Louis, it's pushing
in to Cincinnati now
and the leading edge of that has all
turned over to snow, and
that's what we expect
to see in all our area
as early as six o'clock.
Again, south west to north east.
You can see the blue showing all the snow
that's around our area,
and this will continue for a few hours.
Watch this, the pink, and our model
brings that in right about 11 o'clock.
Now, this did update
just a little while ago,
and it holds the snow in
just a little bit longer
so, maybe that changeover
is closer to the noon hour.
But this is where we start
to see the sleet coming in,
the little ice pellets
that tick on your window.
At two o'clock, DC looks
like it will be able to rain,
we still have a bit of snow
in north eastern Maryland.
but all of this may be icing and sleet
and freezing rain may begin to accumulate.
A quarter inch of ice could be
a problem for many
areas as we work our way
through the early part of the afternoon.
Eventually, it's all rain.
Especially by the time
of the evening rush hour,
but there will be pockets
where there is still
lingering, freezing rain, there always is,
and that's where we
worry about accumulation
on trees and limbs that could present
some power outages and certainly some
tricky travel in those areas.
Here's our 10 o'clock future cast.
It's mostly rain, and
by the time we get to
Thursday morning at 7
a.m. it is out of here.
If you haven't seen this before,
generally we're going
for a three to five inch
snow fall amount, especially
through the Metro area.
Could be closer to the three inch amount
if the changeover happens sooner.
Five inch amount if that
changeover happens later.
We think the heavier snow,
five to eight inches out here,
where there will also be a problem
with ice in the afternoon,
maybe you'll get a quarter inch out there.
One to three inches south and
east for southern Maryland.
Comparing models, that's
what we're putting out there.
Yesterday, this model was very aggressive
with snow, it did come down today,
but this is still a
pretty significant snow,
the American model, and
last thing I'll show
you here is the European model.
It's been sticking with a less impactful
snow part of the storm, but still can see
the ice in the afternoon and this is
two and a half to six
inches around the area.
So, we feel pretty good that those numbers
are going to be what we end up getting.
But we know it's going to
be a messy day regardless,
and Thursday we start to
melt it off, 49 degrees.
Friday we continue the melting.
We do have rain on Saturday,
with a temperature of 44.
We could see the rain linger
in to the first part of Sunday,
but I think most of the day Sunday
is going to be milder
and eventually pretty dry at 64 degrees.
Monday it's sunny.
Tuesday we have another
chance of a rain-snow mix
that we have to keep an eye on.
With a temperature of 47 on Tuesday.
We'll be watching that one closely
and you can continue to monitor that,
as well as other developments as we work
our way, hour by hour, through a tricky
Wednesday around here that could really
be problematic on the roads by downloading
the FOX 5 Weather App.
Sian, back to you.
- Space, that's the next step,
and we have to be prepared.
- [Sian] President Trump's goal to add
a sixth branch to the military
is a step closer to becoming reality.
Today, we signed a directive
to establish the space force.
If approved by congress,
the branch would be allowed, excuse me
would allow the department of defense
to handle all space operations.
- [Sarah] Former president Barack Obama
turning up at an event
at Oakland, California.
He was joined by basketball
star, Steph Curry,
singer John Legend and others to empower
young men of color.
It's a first of its kind
summit, called MBK Rising.
If you remember, the former president
started My Brother's
Keeper several years back.
He says so much can be
accomplished through mentorship.
- I did not grow up and
become the person I am
until I was less focused on me,
and I was more focused
on, how could I be useful?
Who could I help?
- [Sarah] Mr Obama says
being a positive influence
on someone can be beneficial to you
because it also gives you the confidence
when they succeed.
so it's kind of a pay it
forward thing going on there.
- I like it.
- Mm.
- Yep.
Florida's home to oranges,
home to Disney World,
and also home to some
usually bizarre news.
- Straight ahead, we're gonna show you
how one officer was able to round up
some furry fugitives.
("Bad Boys" by Bob Marley)
- [Announcer] Do, do your thing.
Flee that nest.
Seize that moment.
Find your inspiration.
Be extraordinary.
Spread your wings,
and experience the Mazda CX5,
with new signature tramp and turbo.
Mazda,
Feel alive.
- Alexa, play weekend mix.
- [Announcer] The new Lincoln MKC.
Connecting the world inside,
with the world outside.
So you can move through both
a little easier.
Introducing the well connected,
2019 Lincoln MKC.
For a limited time, lease the Lincoln MKC
for only 309 a month,
only at your Lincoln dealer.
- [Announcer] Teacher.
Musician.
Author.
Maybe even a future president.
We never really know who we might
be driving around, do we?
So, that's why we give our cars
advanced safety features.
It's why we give them enduring quality.
It's why we give it everything.
Get 4000 total cash on the purchase
of a new 2019 Sorento V6
at KIA's Presidents Day sales event.
Head to your local KIA today.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] There's a lot to smile about
in every Volkswagen.
Hurry in this Presidents Day,
and lease a 2019 Jetta
S for just 159 a month.
Now with a people-first warranty.
- Here's your Buick, sir.
- Actually, that's my Buick.
- Your Buick doesn't have a roof rack.
- This is my Buick.
- How are we gonna fit in your moms Buick?
- Easy.
- I like that new Buick.
- Me, too.
- I was actually talking about that Buick.
- I knew that.
- Did you?
- [Announcer] Buick's fresh new line up
is full of surprises.
Get great deals on our
expectation shattering line.
Pay no interest for 72
months on most Buick models.
(upbeat music)
- Woo!
- I'm looking at that truck.
- Wow!
- That's awesome.
- [Announcer] Everyone is excited about
the all-new, award-winning Chevy models.
- They're all really cool cars.
- Woo, I love it.
- I can't stop staring at it.
- [Announcer] See what the excitement's
all about at your local Chevy dealer
and take advantage of
a great deal like this.
Current, qualified, competitive lessees
can lease this Malibu
for around 179 a month.
Or, current GM owners get 4250
total cash allowance on most Malibu models
when you purchase and
finance with GM financial.
- An officer was on patrol when he
came across a herd of Billy goats.
Herded them home, where they had knocked
down the fence, this
in Florida by the way,
in case you cared, whatever.
- [Announcer] Visit your Washington DC
BMW Center for a test drive today.
BMW, the ultimate driving machine.
- [Man] Everyone knows the five senses.
- [Woman] but what if we told you,
- [Man] There's more.
(car engine hums)
An illusive sensation.
- [Woman] Coax tiled only
under ideal circumstances.
- [Man] We can't fully describe it.
But you'll know it.
- [Woman] When you feel it.
- [Man] We call it
the ultimate driving machine.
Pre it now, from February 28th
and receive acception to
Presidents Day offers.
- [Announcer] Honda of Chantilly
has declared prices and payments are down
during our Honda President's Day sale.
Get new Hondas at 0%
financing for 60 months.
And new Civics are only 169 a month.
Find your best deal now
at hondaofchantilly.com.
- [Announcer] It's time to go.
Toyota Go.
With a redesigned, all new 2019 RAV4,
available with all wheel drive.
And the latest multimedia system,
compatible with Apple CarPlay,
Amazon Alexa and Wi-Fi.
Now, lease the RAV for only 219 a month
or finance with Toyota and get 1000
towards your down payment.
Plus, the piece of mind that comes
with having all these advanced
safety features standard.
Go see your Toyota dealer today.
Toyota, let's go places.
- [Announcer] See, feel, climb,
first out, last in.
Look round corners,
look in crannies,
go down dark alleys,
lose yourself,
catch a lift,
push boundaries,
go walk about,
get set,
go after the goosebumps,
never stop discovering.
The Land Rover Discovery
and Discovery Sport.
The only adventure sales
event is happening now.
Land Rover, above and beyond.
- Do you think this is fun for me?
You think I'm having fun?
- [Man] But it certainly wasn't having fun
(mumbling)
- [Man] Do you have eyes on the target?
- [Woman] Is it her?
- [Man] I can't tell from these photos,
I need better shots.
- Thank you for flying Turkish Airlines.
(intense music)
- Taxi!
- [Man] You waiting for someone?
- Nope, just looking.
(intense music)
- [Announcer] The Hyundai Presidents Day
sales event is going on now.
Get huge savings on our full line up
of cars and SUVs.
Hyundai is also making
some history of its own.
The Hyundai Kona has been named
the 2019 North American
Utility Vehicle of the Year.
Incredible vehicles, monumental savings.
Find yours during the Hyundai
Presidents Day sales event,
going on now.
Get an Elantra, starting at 15,400,
or get up to 2300 cash back.
Now extended an extra 500 for government
employees affected by the shut down.
During Honda of Chantilly's
President's Day sale,
zero down payment and
zero security deposit,
put you in this all wheel drive CR-V
for 299 a month.
That's a low payment.
And this new Accord is priced even lower.
Look for the giant wind turbine
and huge Honda savings
at Honda of Chantilly.
- Coming up on the Final
5, did the President.