- [Announcer] Rates as low as
2.74 annual percentage rate
and get up to $300 in rebates
on GAP insurance and extended warranty.
Visit MoneyOneFCU.org today.
- [Announcer] The all new WSUA9 app,
coming soon to the App Store.
(energetic music)
- Good morning and welcome
to Great Day Washington.
I'm Markette Sheppard.
Kristen is out today but if you're at home
and you're looking for a mate,
we've got some great digital dating tips
for you this morning.
Plus we're sharing how a
group of local scientists
are working hard to combat the pollution
in the Potomac which is so important
as we get that storm runoff this morning.
But first, let's get over
to WUSA9 meteorologist,
Howard Bernstein, for an update
on this flash flood warning
we're currently experiencing, Howard?
- Yeah, Markette, we've been tracking
some very heavy rainfall
over the last few hours.
It came out of Frederick
then moved right down to 70.
These are flood warnings from Frederick
in towards Southern
Prince George's County.
So much of the area under
active flash flood warnings
and these are the worst, most dangerous
type of flooding we can have,
because flash flooding
happens very quickly.
It could catch you by surprise
and it only takes a
foot, two feet of water,
to push your car off the road.
So that's why you hear
turn around, don't drown.
The good news is that up
in Frederick at least,
the heaviest rains are done,
but even Howard County now under
a flash flood warning 'til 11:45.
Montgomery County on the East Side,
seeing some heavier rains,
but the heaviest rains,
and Mary and I were looking at this,
some of the precip intensities,
the rainfall intensities
are in the five plus inches
per hour in the heaviest parts,
so these are tropical downpours
causing some flash flooding.
Not everywhere, but there've
been a number of water rescues
already in Frederick
and Montgomery Counties.
You see along I-66 and South
seems to be the heaviest.
Silver Spring, you're starting to see,
not quite as heavy rain move in
but everywhere you see orange and red,
very, very heavy rainfall for Fedex Field
right across the heart of D.C.
Now moving down toward Alexandria here,
just about to Franconia.
So our friends down in
Mount Vernon and Lowertown
and areas of Prince George's County
outside the Beltway there.
Just generally South of Joint Base Andrews
over toward Clinton and
Melwood and Upper Marlboro,
get ready as this whole mass of water
is moving down towards you
with that flash flood warning until 11:15,
and Prince George's County,
and we are gonna see better weather.
Once we get rid of this
stuff this morning,
we'll see the activity shift
off to the South and West
as we get into the afternoon.
So the next one to two hours
could be particularly bad with flooding
but it will get better
this afternoon, Ellen.
- I hope so 'cause the roads
are not looking good right now.
This is a live look at the Beltway.
We had a closure here.
They've just opened a second left lane
on the inner loop of the the Beltway
by the American Legion Bridge.
Let me show you some of the backups
because this has been
going on for a while.
It sounds like there was a
tree that fell onto a vehicle,
caused some sort of accident.
They're trying to move it over
to the right hand side
as quickly as possible
but you can see from that camera,
that's what traffic looks like,
trying to head around the
inner loop of the Beltway.
You're jammed coming from
the Springfield interchange.
This is my maps to show
you some of the delays.
I-270 southbound, not looking good.
The Beltway is not looking good,
and I'm also now seeing
reports in North Arlington
of several flooded
streets that we're having
some water rescues with.
We've had many rescues
up in Frederick as well,
following Frederick County,
their police department's Twitter page.
They've been just tweeting
out closures like crazy.
These are just the main streets,
not even the side streets.
Definitely impacting you
as you head out the door.
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
- We got the gold!
All right, now to your top
headlines this morning.
The U.S. Women's Soccer Team,
they got quite the welcome last night
when they returned to
their hotel in France.
The U.S. captured its fourth
Women's World Cup title
in a two to nothing win
over the Netherlands.
Captain Megan Rapinoe scored
the first goal of the match
and was named the tournament's
outstanding player.
New York City Mayor, Bill de Blasio,
he invited the players
to a ticker tape parade
in Manhattan's Canyon
of Heroes on Wednesday.
Developing this morning,
there was panic inside Union Station
after loud bangs were
mistaken for gunshots.
Police are now telling us it appears
that this was all just fireworks.
The incident happened shortly
before five last night,
and many people took to social
media to document the chaos.
One guys said he looked for exit signs
and walked out the back of a store
with some other customers.
Other people said they hid
in the storage closets and restrooms
until they were given the all clear.
- It's crazy and we live in a society,
not only in America but
all across the world,
when we hear unexpected sounds,
it draws our attention to
what could possibly be,
and fortunately, unfortunately,
it's just the type of
times that we live in.
It scares people.
It scares people because you never know,
especially after 9/11.
You really never know what's gonna happen.
- Now the panic caused a stampede.
Three people were treated at
the scene for minor injuries.
When it comes to the person
who set off the fireworks,
police tell us they are investigating
but would not say if someone was arrested.
However, with all of those
cameras inside and outside,
it is likely at this point,
they know how this was carried
out and who is responsible.
Meanwhile, mistaking fireworks
for gunshots, this isn't new.
Just last week, fireworks
sparked a stampede
at Navy Pier in Chicago.
Police there say a
private security officer
mistook the sounds of gunfire, as gunfire,
and shouted for everyone to take cover.
At least 13 people were
taken to the hospital
after being trampled.
Well, in a sweet story this morning,
some pictures of a little boy helping out
an Honor Guard member in Arlington, Texas,
they're going viral.
The police department posted the pictures
of 11 year old, Josh Brown,
tying Officer Wilson's shoe
at the 4th of July parade
that was held in the city.
Wilson noticed his shoe was untied
and his fellow officers
asked Josh to tie the shoe.
Josh said he was a little bit nervous,
but he got the job done.
The next day, Officer Wilson
thanked him for helping out.
Josh says he hopes to be a
police officer when he grows up.
Maryland voters will soon
have a new gender option
on voter registration forms.
Last week, the Board of
Elections agreed to list X
as a gender option along with
M for male and F for female.
The change mirrors a new Maryland
law for drivers' licenses
and state issued ID cards.
That law goes into effect on October 1st.
We also want to say a big congratulations
to the "Real Housewives of
Potomac" star, Ashley Darby.
She and her husband, Michael,
they welcomed a baby boy
into the world yesterday.
Ashley Darby posted on Instagram,
"It was the most sensational
day of our shared life."
She's yet to reveal the baby boy's name
and we are all waiting for that.
Congratulations to them.
I was her Miss America roommate.
I never thought I'd get to
announce her first child on air.
That's great.
Congratulations, Ashley.
Now we're gonna send
things out to Andi Hauser
who is braving the rain this
morning out in Alexandria.
How are you doing?
- Hey, good morning to you.
I'm doing well.
I mean, I'm soaking wet.
Originally this morning,
we were gonna be out there.
We were talking about the Province
which is that old tall ship that's now,
it has the permanent home
here at Founder's Park,
but in light of things,
since there's so many warnings and watches
for flooding in the area,
we wanted to go ahead and show you
what things are like
right here in Alexandria
and as you can see,
rain is certainly coming down.
It's coming down in buckets
and of course, there are
many streets in this area
that are prone to flooding,
especially when we were in
that flash flood situation.
So, already, you know, you can
tell there's nobody out here
and for good reason.
People have gone ahead and
either found some shelter.
But again guys, it is
certainly coming down.
We could just see it before it got here.
Just that dark line,
and it just continued to
move closer and closer
over the last 30 minutes, which
is where we are right now.
It seems like we are
right in the thick of it
here at Founder's Park
in Old Town Alexandria.
So, I'm gonna step in for a second,
dry off a little bit,
try and get the drops off my hat.
In the meantime, let's
send it back to the ladies
in the nice dry studio.
Back to you.
- [Announcer] The dating scene is trickier
than ever in the digital age.
Coming up, best selling author, Andi Lew,
will help you find better
dates on your device.
(bright music)
- Everyone wants to buy houses these days,
but whom can you trust?
Call Express Homebuyers.
Thousands of homeowners have trusted us
to buy their house the hassle free way.
♪ Express Homebuyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
- A great man once said,
"Knowledge is power,"
so I want to give it to you.
I'm attorney Paul Samakow
and I've written a book
that you and your family need to have.
What to do before and then,
if an auto accident happens,
so you'll be protected
and so you don't end up
on the short end of the stick.
Go to AccidentLawBook.com,
and download it instantly for free.
That's AccidentLawBook.com,
and yes, if you need
to talk, ask questions,
and certainly, if you need me,
me or one of my attorneys
will answer the phone.
That's right, an attorney
answers the phone when you call.
I'm attorney Paul Samakow
and my team can help.
Call one of my five million numbers,
and an attorney will answer.
(light acoustic music)
Your case probably isn't worth
five million, by the way,
but phone numbers are easy to remember.
♪ Deal boss ♪
- Are you tired of overpaying
those outlandish monthly fees
for your cable or satellite bill?
I'm Matt Granite.
I cut the cord and this is my favorite
Deal Boss Deal of the Week,
an antenna that will get
your more free TV channels
than anything else on the market.
This first of its kind
antenna installs in seconds
and is my favorite way to cut the cord.
I found it for half price
and it's waiting for you.
♪ Deal boss ♪
- Go to DealBoss.tv for a link to this
and other great deals.
- The only thing that
I would do differently,
the only thing,
I should've called
Express Homebuyers sooner.
♪ Express Homebuyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days. ♪
- Well, welcome back to
Great Day Washington.
Now we're gonna talk about
digital dating in the social age
with an author of a book who
tried it out for herself,
and she wants to save you
from some digital disasters.
Andi Lew, welcome to Great Day Washington.
- Thank you, Markette.
When I was researching when
dating apps first came about.
Four years, it took me to
research and write this book
and I found that from
this swipe left culture,
people really want meaningful connections
and so this is the ultimate
dating wellness book
because I'm a certified
wellness and lifestyle coach.
I want you to be able to find love.
- And people are happier and
healthier the research says,
when they do have a mate,
but how do you do it nowadays
when it seems like everything starts out
in a digital relationship?
You're not meeting people
face to face anymore.
- Well Markette, you know what?
It's just so handy.
I mean, given on a day like
today you want to be indoors
or you're a single mom and
you just can't get out.
We like to do everything
from our phone, so why not?
However, we need to be careful,
as to how we put ourselves on the market
in this singles market,
because there are some
things that you can do,
which I explain, to help you
have a meaningful connection
and something that is safe.
- Okay, and so to do the research,
you actually went
undercover for this book.
(laughing)
What does that mean?
- Well most of the time, I
didn't tell them who I was,
and I wanted to experience dating life
as a newly divorced
sort of woman in her 40s
and how it's so hard to navigate
through this world of digital dating.
It's hard to keep up,
and I wanted to be able to help others.
But other times, I did say,
"Listen, I'm just an author
and I'm researching."
And a lot of the people
would reply back and say,
"Oh, that's a really good line.
"I'm gonna use that line."
I said, "No, I really am."
- [Markette] And so they still
wanted to go out with you?
So when you say them, you
mean you were dating men
and interacting with men for the book?
- [Andi] Yes.
- But sometimes you told
them you were doing research
and sometimes you just,
and what was the barometer?
If you were interested
maybe you didn't tell them?
- Well, what I did was I kinda said,
"Look, this really is research.
"Tell me about your experience
"because I would love to write about it
"and help other people."
And they said, "Well, can
we go on a date first?
"And then can I be in the book?"
And I said, "Honey, you already are.
"I've been screenshotting everything."
- Wow, okay.
- So there's some great stories in there
but I did cover up their identity
with a bit of a cowboy emoji
or something like that.
- Okay, so it's anonymous.
Now, nowadays, everybody
if they're interested,
they wanna like slide someone a DM.
- Yeah.
- And you say those days are done.
Can you explain?
- Well look, people are
going into direct messages
on Instagram as well as dating apps.
You don't need to court via a dating app.
It can be actually through
any sort of social media
and I wanted to explain
the correct netiquette,
if you like, on how to do that.
- Okay, internet etiquette?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Okay, so you're saying you don't need
to sign up on a proper
dating app to date anymore.
You can use any social media platform,
but you have some rules of engagement.
- Well, that's right.
First of all, people are
getting others' attention
by going on, what I call, a liking spree.
So on Instagram, for example,
they'll like a couple
of the photos at the top
and then maybe scroll down
to sort of a month prior,
and then a bit of a follow.
And that kinda gets
your attention, I guess,
when it comes up in the
notifications in your newsfeed.
And if you like the look of the person,
then you might slide into their DMs,
and then a conversation begins.
- Okay, so go on a,
so you, do you recommend this?
Go on a liking spree, do
a nice comment and follow,
and then it comes up,
like, this person's name
like 10 times and you're--
- Well, not 10 times Markette,
'cause then you're gonna
look like a crazy person.
- Right? That's why I'm asking
if you would recommend it.
- That's right.
- Okay.
- So I'd probably recommend
about two to three times and a follow.
And then--
- You said spree.
So a spree is two to three likes.
- Yeah, a liking spree is two to three.
That's a healthy way,
and you know what?
It's healthy to flirt,
and to do it safely and
with the right netiquette,
if you like, is the best way.
- Okay, that's good.
So not all attempts at digital
dating go according to plan
as we know in real life
face to face dating.
So, how do you avoid the disasters?
Or you do, maybe you're
not a weirdo or a crazy,
but you come across as one
because you liked too many photos.
- That's why you need my book.
- Right, right.
- Because there is a chapter called,
"How to Weed Out the Weirdos."
Are they weird or are they
just socially awkward?
I mean, this didn't come
with a book of rules,
so I wrote one, and it's
important to know sort of
how you are coming across as you say,
and there are ways to
come across, you know,
really authentic and kind,
and things like that,
and you can have a very, you know,
people are getting married out
of these sorts of dating apps.
So it's important to know
that if you present well,
then you'll attract well.
- Okay, you said a good tip before.
We have to go to break,
but I just wanna share.
You said if you see someone on
Instagram and you like them,
try to do, like, a Facetime
or a Skype right away.
- Good, yeah.
- To make sure,
and then you have a book
launch event in town.
Can you tell folks about it?
- Yeah, that's right.
So basically I'd love you
to follow me on Instagram,
and you can see all the details.
Also, you do need to
bring it to a video call
because then you can see
if they're a fake person or a real person,
but learn how to block
their number as well
when you do do a video call.
- All right. Thank you so much, Andi Lew.
The book is called,
"#InstaLovers: Digital Dating,
"DM Disasters and Love Stories."
- And it's on Amazon.
- And it's on Amazon!
We'll be back with more
Great Day after this.
Thank you.
- [Announcer] Up next, we
meet a group of scientists,
who are working hard
to prevent the pollution in the Potomac.
- [Female] I am a nurse.
- [Male] A firefighter.
- [Male] A college student.
- [Female] A mother.
- [Female] And I am an American soldier.
- [Female] I will always be ready.
- [Male] For every storm.
- [Male] And disaster that
threatens my community.
- [Male] I will always be
there to protect my neighbors.
- [Female] My family.
- [Male] And my country.
- [Female] We are the Army National Guard.
- [Male] We are the Army National Guard.
- [Narrator] Visit nationalguard.com
to learn more about part-time service.
- If you're like most
people, you love your pets.
Now is a great time to replace your floor
with our certified pet-friendly products
during our free installation sale.
Plus, save an extra $100
with promo code, "Home Improvement."
♪ Call 877-50-FLOOR, ♪
♪ Pick up the phone, we'll
be knocking at your door ♪
(dog barks)
It's buyback time at McCarthy Services.
For a limited time, McCarthy Services
will buy back your old,
inefficient HVAC system
when we take up to $1,500 off
your new heating and
cooling system purchase.
That's right!
You'll save up to $1,500
when you choose the professionals
at McCarthy Services.
Call McCarthy Services today
to set up your complimentary
HVAC system analysis.
McCarthy Services, heating,
cooling, and plumbing.
Making it work, making it right.
Visit McCarthyHomeServices.com.
♪ McCarthyHomeServices.com ♪
- [Announcer] Jiffy Lube
Live Concert Calendar
presented by Live Nation.
(energetic music)
July 9th, Rockstar
Energy Disrupt Festival,
featuring The Used and Thrice.
July 11th, Blink-182 and Lil Wayne.
July 13th, Dierks Bentley.
July 14th, Kidz Bop.
For VIP, box and season tickets,
visit livenationpremiumseats.com.
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm Dan from MarketPro Homebuyers
and we want to buy your home.
- MarketPro Homebuyers
gave us a fair offer
and truly helped my family.
Call us today at 301-799-7355.
- [Narrator] This is Annie.
(phone buzzing)
- [Audience Member] Shh.
- [Announcer] And this is Annie
paying back her friend for the tickets
with Zelle before the previews start.
And this is Annie getting
ready to enjoy the show.
This is your right here right now bank.
This is Wells Fargo.
- Upgrade your home fast and save.
Free installation from 50 Floor
on all carpet, hardwood,
vinyl and laminate.
Offer ends at the end of
the month so call now.
Plus save an extra $100 with promo code,
"Home Improvement."
♪ Call 877-50-Floor ♪
♪ Pick up the phone, we'll
be knocking at your door ♪
- Hey, welcome back to
Great Day Washington.
This morning, we are coming to you live
from Old Town Harbor,
where the rain is coming down,
but I wanted to tell you,
earlier this week, we
had a chance to catch up
with the folks from the River,
Potomac Riverkeepers Foundation,
and when it comes to water quality
after a major weather event like this,
things are gonna be compromised,
so here's what you need to know.
Check it out.
- We have our annual report.
- Thank you.
- [Woman] If you'd like to grab one.
- [Andi] One by one,
volunteers signed up here
at the National Harbor.
- We just felt that it
was really important
that the public had an opportunity
to know when the water was safe to go in.
- [Andi] To learn how they can help heal
the waters of the Potomac River.
- We are launching our
Virginia and Maryland
Citizen Science Volunteer Water
Quality Monitoring Program,
Educating them about where sources
of bacteria are coming from,
how they get into the river,
and the public health risks
where people go in the river
and don't know when it's safe
to go in the water or not.
- [Andi] Dean Naujoks
from the Potomac River Keeper Network
helped launch this program
because there was little
to no data recorded
on the bacteria found in the Potomac.
- [Dean] Rule of thumb
is one to three days
after a rain event,
usually you will have
high levels of bacteria.
- That bacteria comes
from backed up sewage
and storm drains that
spill into the river.
Is there a specific type of bacteria
that we're looking for?
- That's right.
It's E. coli.
That's the main test we're using.
The reason we use E. Coli
is it's somewhat correlated
with human health issues.
From what I understand,
that's why there is a swimming
ban in the D.C. waters.
- [Andi] Patrick Fletcher
is a volunteer scientist
with the Potomac Riverkeeper Network
and donates his time to help collect data.
He showed us the process.
- [Patrick] I'm gonna just
scoop this in like that,
fill it up.
Now we have a clean sample
of the Potomac right here.
- [Andi] They also test the turbidity
or clarity of the water and the pH levels.
We don't have to go far
to process the data.
The Sea Dog, a boat donated
to the Potomac Riverkeepers
serves as a live working
science lab right on the water.
- [Patrick] So if it's fluorescent,
it means that there, it's
positive for E. coli.
- [Andi] The Riverkeepers then compare
the numbers to a chart to determine
if the sample is a pass or a fail.
- [Patrick] In the D.C. region,
we're using a conservative cut off of 126,
so this would be a fail.
- All the data collected by the volunteers
can be downloaded to your phone
by using the Swim Guide app.
The goal is to let us
know if the water is safe
for a variety of activities.
- We're gonna be uploading it here
every single week on Fridays,
so that when people are
going out on the weekends
during warm weather months,
September through October,
they know based on that
data that we took that day,
whether the water is safe or not to swim.
A swimmable Potomac River is the goal.
- [Andi] Currently,
there are 10 test sites
along the river, but Dean is optimistic
there will be more as the program grows.
His hope is that this program pushes out
the pollution problem in the Potomac.
- We're seeing important things happening,
like upgrades to sewage treatment plants.
- [Andi] After all, it's
about keeping the water clean
for generations to come.
- [Dean] I can honestly say
that this river is gonna be cleaner
probably in 10 years
from now than it is now.
- All right, guys.
If you want more information,
you can log on to WUSA9.com
but again, I'm out here in
Alexandria this morning.
We're actually at Old Town Harbor.
You can really feel the dock moving.
It seems like the wind's
even picking up a little bit
but the rain, definitely coming down.
So as you heard there in the story,
you're gonna wanna
allow three or four days
for the bacteria levels and E. coli levels
to possibly drop in the
river before going into it,
or utilizing it in any way.
Let's send it back to
the ladies in the studio.
- [Announcer] We're
going gaga for gazpacho
in the Great Day Kitchen.
Coming up, find out where you can get
the summer dish all month long.
(energetic music)
- Flooding rains continue
across Washington and Point South now.
New flash flood warnings
for D.C. until 11:15,
that also goes with south
toward Prince George's County.
Some of the rainfall rates here,
three, four, five inches per hour.
We'll take a closer look at radar
and let you know what you can expect
for the rest of your Monday and the week,
in just a couple of minutes.
- Are you looking for a
hassle free, simple way
to sell your home as is?
We buy houses directly.
There's no middle-men, no commissions.
Give us a call today.
House Buyers of America.
Real estate made real easy.
- With Cox, you get
everything you wanna watch
in one place using the voice remote.
- Show me action.
- Even a ninny like me can figure it out.
With streaming apps, you miss live events,
and waste time searching for shows.
- Not this one, that one?
- It's clear that Cox is the better choice
just like it's clear
that the teleprompter guy
thinks I'm a booboohead
who steals parking spots.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Get live TV,
great apps and on demand
from Cox starting at $79.99 a month.
- Hi friends.
Do you know what I don't like?
Liars.
Insurance company liars.
Insurance company adjusters
who avoid your calls,
rarely call you back,
who stall, delay and
do everything they can
to frustrate you in connection
with your accident claim.
And then, they offer you
a ridiculously insulting
amount of money while telling
you the bills were too high,
that you didn't need
all of that treatment,
and that you really
weren't hurt that badly.
So what can you do?
The system is not set up, unfortunately,
in a way that allows you to do much.
You can't file a lawsuit and
push them, but a lawyer can.
I'm attorney Paul Samakow,
and the antics of the insurance
industry really piss me off.
So when I represent you,
if I don't get what I
want for you, lawsuit.
Call one of my five million
numbers if you've been injured.
An attorney will answer.
That's right, an attorney
will answer your call.
(light music)
- Into the afternoon.
If you see high water and you don't know
if the road is there, assume it is not.
It's just very dangerous.
Now, the future cast.
I do wanna point out, I think
this is about 20 or 30 miles
too far North because it's got the rain
still in Montgomery County,
but we've seen the heaviest down here so,
assume this is just a
little bit too far North
but even at 11:30, we still
have some heavier rains,
potentially coming in
to the South Side of DC.
The nice thing is, the trend
shows the rain moving south
and then southwest as we
get into the afternoon.
So through the morning,
we still have a threat for
some heavy tropical downpours
but then in the afternoon,
we'll see some sun as we dry out
with highs staying in the 70s to low 80s.
Much more comfortable out there,
but a dangerous situation at the moment.
Scattered showers and storms this morning.
Some of them heavy, heavy rain,
so please watch out for the high water.
Mostly in the--
- Then it must be good.
- Yeah, yeah.
Totally, yeah.
- Right.
- So it's about, like raw vegetables,
so basically it's like
a vegetable smoothie.
Gazpacho, the base of
it, is tomato usually,
traditionally in Spain,
but we're gonna play with that
to base on what's in season.
So right now, we're
gonna do green chickpea
and cucumber gazpacho is
what we're gonna make.
- Oh, this is nice.
This is really--
- Yes, it's super healthy.
Green chickpea?
- It's not dairy free though so.
- Right.
It's not dairy free but
yogurt is one of those foods
where they're on the health food list
as something that--
- Exactly.
That you can eat.
- It's good for you.
- It's full fat Greek yogurt.
It's not low fat which is the best.
- Full fat?
- Full fat.
- [Markette] Okay, there you go.
- Don't go for the low cal stuff.
- These green chickpeas look amazing.
- Yeah, so they're fresh green chickpeas.
- They're one of my favorite foods,
but this is the type of summer soup
that they eat along the Mediterranean,
so that's Spain and--
- Yeah, that, so it's the southern part
of the inner Lucia region,
is like where gazpacho kinda started.
- Okay.
- So obviously, tomato is a base but,
I mean, we have the grilled
local peach, piquillo pepper.
- So this is another.
- Gazpacho.
So you have four different,
so it's a different gazpacho each week,
and this one is made
from Virginia peaches.
- So local Virginia peaches,
grilled and then we puree
it with piquillo peppers.
- [Markette] That's
beautiful, what's this?
- [Matt] And then yellow tomato,
and yellow watermelon gazpacho.
- [Markette] Yellow, I've
never seen a yellow watermelon.
Our camera is slowly panning there.
- [Matt] This is the
hybridized watermelon.
It's super sweet, it's delicious.
- [Markette] Any different tastes or?
- [Matt] It's a little more
sweeter, I feel like it is.
- [Markette] Oh really?
Oh.
- [Matt] Yeah, and they kind
of, there's tomato in that,
so it kind of balances out.
- Okay, beautiful.
- There's acid.
There's sweetness so it's nice.
- Okay.
Let's get back to this one.
- So let's dig in.
So you got, we got the
red, we got the yellow,
now we're making the green.
- And the green, exactly.
- Gazpacho, okay.
I wanna go every week,
just to say I had a healthy meal
at least once a week, Chef Matt.
- All right, so high protein.
You got the avocados.
- Okay.
- All right.
Lemon juice, lemon zest.
- Nice little twang there.
- Little bit of sherry vinegar
for a little more acid, which is so good.
All right, so what
binds it is the avocado,
the cheese, and the yogurt.
So you don't have to
put any bread into it.
- That's nice.
- So it will not,
it will not separate.
And there's no crazy food
chemicals in it as well.
- [Markette] Oh, that's so great.
And then the bread helps you
stay slim and trim and light
in summer as well.
- Exactly.
- [Markette] But full
because of the chickpeas.
- [Matt] Exactly.
So jalapenos, because everybody
likes spicy food in the summertime.
Fresh mint, and obviously
a lot of green herbs
to make it green, and then basil.
And then water to thin it out,
to get whatever consistency you want.
You can add more or less water.
So fresh still water 'cause
it won't effect the flavor.
It's nice and neutral.
There's no chlorine or any
chemicals or whatever in it.
- [Markette] Ah, okay.
So that's why you use that.
- [Matt] Yes, it won't
affect the flavor at all.
- [Markette] So we're
stirring this up on TV,
but at home if you were to
attempt this, what would you use?
- [Matt] So at home,
you would use a blender,
obviously to puree it,
and then if you want it chunky or smooth,
you can pass it through
a china cap or a chinois
to get it whatever texture
you want, but it's open ended.
You can eat it like this
if you want. (laughs)
- [Markette] Uh, okay no thank you.
I'll just keep stirring
this and as you continue.
(laughing)
Okay, so imagine.
- It's like yogurt soup.
- [Markette] Imagine you have a blender
and all of these ingredients,
get nice and smooth with no lumps,
like you chefs do so well.
How would it look when
you finally plate it?
- [Matt] So, we're gonna plate it.
This is how we do at the restaurant.
A little bit of tzatziki, so
dill, cucumber, Greek yogurt,
and if you want, you can
do the rest gluten-free.
I like a little breadcrumbs for texture.
- Just a little.
- Just a little bit.
- [Markette] And it's also
very beautiful on the plate.
- [Matt] All right, a lot of olive oil,
'cause they're Mediterranean,
they love olive oil and olives,
and then pour tableside.
Nice and smooth, see that
little texture to it.
- [Markette] Oh, so that's nice.
So the waiter comes out and pours it?
- [Matt] Yeah, we pour it tableside.
- [Markette] At your seat,
I love when they do that.
- [Matt] And I'll put
some more olive oil on,
'cause olive oil is really good.
(Markette laughs)
And that's it.
- [Markette] All right, that's beautiful.
Now, I would probably do this.
I love breadcrumbs, could you do that?
- [Matt] Yeah, you can
do whatever you want.
- Just like a little.
- Yeah.
(Markette humming)
- And then like a little?
- Little bit of microgreens.
- [Markette] Yeah exactly,
'cause then I can say
that I ate my vegetables,
and no one knows it's a tablespoon full.
Now what's great about Olivia,
is you have this torta de
gazpacho or gazpacho de torta,
depending on which order you eat it.
So if the soup is just not
enough, you have something more.
- Yeah, so it's similar to a combo plate.
For 16 bucks you can come in,
and get whatever weekly gazpacho we have,
little village salad, and
a little burrata sandwich.
- That looks so amazing.
- Little bit of pan-cooked
tomate on the bottom.
- Wow, so the burrata's
like nice and soft,
and then you squeeze it and then.
- Yeah, it just oozes out.
- It just oozes out all over.
Can y'all see that at home?
Okay, I'm gonna leave it here,
but look at that burrata.
And then you squeeze it
when you bite into it,
and you're like, it's the best
meal I ever had in my life!
Okay, so four different gazpachos.
One each week, where do
we find you for more?
- So 800 F Street Northwest.
- 800 F Street.
- So Penn Quarter and not
Chinatown, where Penn Quarter is.
- All right, there you go, 800 F Street.
Say hi to Chef Matt if you stop by,
and we'll be back with
more Great Day after this.
(bright music)
Did you know you can lease HVAC systems,
water heaters, and generators?
Find out how with Michael
and Son, coming up.
- [Announcer] Diamonds at
their lowest price in years.
Half carat Solitaires are
now $399, one carat $790,
two carats $950 per carat
plus one carat studs $399.
Insane prices on thousands
of GIA Diamonds and designer rings.
Buy direct, the Jewelry Exchange Bethesda.
- [Narrator] This is Annie.
(phone buzzes)
- [Audience Member] Shh.
- [Narrator] And this is
Annie paying back her friend
for the tickets with Zelle
before the previews start.
And this is Annie getting
ready to enjoy the show.
This is your right here, right now bank.
This is Wells Fargo.
- [Announcer] It's buy back
time at ARS Rescue Rooter.
For a limited time, ARS
Rescue Rooter will buy back
your old inefficient HVAC system
when we take up to $1500 off
your new heating and
cooling system purchase.
That's right, you'll save up to $1500
when you choose the professionals at ARS.
Call ARS Rescue Rooter today
to set up your complimentary
HVAC system analysis.
ARS Rescue Rooter, heating,
cooling, and plumbing.
Making it work, making it right.
Visit ARSofVirginia.com.
♪ Call ARS and Rescue Rooter ♪
- [Announcer] Gutter problems?
But you're confused with all
the claims and free offers.
Most gutter companies
try to upsell you
expensive gutter systems.
Gutter Helmet will prep and
cover your existing gutters,
saving you a ton of money.
Call for a free demonstration and quote.
- You just can't trust
the internet these days.
Luckily, I discovered NordVPN.
Thanks to NordVPN, I
feel so safe online now.
I just click and let NordVPN do the rest.
Who would've thought it takes just a click
to keep the hackers away?
(bright music)
- [Announcer] Diamonds, the forever gift.
The Jewelry Exchange has one
carat certified for $1790.
Two carat rings and studs, $2900.
Two carat certified, $5900.
Thousands of GIA Diamonds and
mountings at insane prices,
plus no interest for 12 months.
The Jewelry Exchange Bethesda.
(energetic music)
(dramatic music)
- [Man] Always, we stay close together.
- Oh.
- Yes.
- [Woman] Oh, they're telling
us to be quiet, sorry.
- [Man] Oh, what's wrong?
(bright music)
(people chattering)
- [Woman] Who's that?
He is wobbling and
weaving, wobbling around.
That would not be the morning
to be out sightseeing.
- Systems when you can get the ease and,
all right, sorry about that.
We'll get back to Howard in just a minute,
but for now we're talking Michael and Son.
When it comes to keeping
systems up in your home,
you can get the ease and convenience
of leasing with Michael and Son.
Here to tell us more about
their leasing programs
is proud son and, sorry
about that I'm blanking here.
Sorry, proud son and
owner of Michael and Son.
Welcome back, Basim Mansour.
- Are we live?
- We are live on TV right now.
- Oh, wonderful.
- I know.
You didn't know, we came quickly.
There was no teleprompter for me to read,
but we are here to talk
about home ownership,
and how leasing an HVAC system
is so convenient and easy.
Tell me more.
- Well, traditionally everybody
normally has HVAC systems
in their home and they
buy them when they go bad.
We have a new product,
and it's called a Lease
Hassle-Free Lease Program,
and with that it means that
you don't own your HVAC system.
Why own an asset that's gonna fail
and it's gonna die over a period time?
Why own a problem?
Why own a maintenance issue?
Lease it.
- And a lot of people don't know
that they can lease their system.
This is like you said, hassle-free.
Tell me more about what
makes it hassle-free.
- What makes it hassle-free
is the fact that you don't
have to think about it.
We take care of all the maintenance.
We take care of the filter changes.
We take care of tuning
it up before the seasons.
We take care of any repairs.
Listen, the truth is,
everything's gonna fail.
These systems are gonna fail.
Everything in life fails,
and when they do fail,
we'll take care of it.
I mean, that's the thing,
and it's not gonna hurt you.
You're not gonna feel
the pain of thinking,
oh my god, what's this gonna cost?
It's covered, it's taken care of.
- That's true, because no one
wants to spend their money,
although you need it,
no one wants to spend their
money buying a new HVAC system.
How much can people
really save by leasing,
especially when you think
about your five to seven years
on a system, it's working
hard in the summer.
- Oh yeah, well you know what?
Actually I'll tell you a very quick story.
I was talking to an elderly lady,
and I was thinking about her,
and I was thinking she was on the fence
whether to lease or to
buy, and I said, "Listen."
I said, "I want you to
lease and I'll tell you why,
"because if I lease it to you,
"I know that you're gonna be covered
"for the rest of your life,
"that no one's gonna
take advantage of you,
"that we're always gonna
take care of your system,
"that no person's gonna come in
"and not do you right with the repairs."
And when you lease it,
you know you're covered, and
that's what you're gonna get.
You're gonna get security,
you're gonna get the knowing
that you don't have to think about it.
You're gonna get the fact
that you don't have to
schedule maintenances,
we do that, you know?
- When you talk about
someone on a fixed income,
like a senior citizen,
who maybe doesn't have the wherewithal
to go out and actually
shop for an HVAC system,
you also offer a convenient monthly price,
so people know what to expect,
and know you're gonna be there for them,
but then they also know what
to expect from month to month.
- Absolutely.
The thing is, when you buy a system,
and if you were to buy that, right?
You think about, you're gonna buy it,
but what you don't think
about is all the repairs
and the maintenance over
the life of the unit.
If you were to take the
repairs and the maintenances,
plus the cost of equipment,
that's a monthly cost,
because those systems are only
gonna last 10 or 15 years.
So, we're just taking that,
and just combining into one fixed payment
where you're guaranteed you're
not gonna have surprises.
- I love this, especially
for new homeowners.
You think about the elderly people,
but then first time homebuyers,
they can be overwhelmed with everything
they have to do for a new home.
So it makes sense,
now but what happens
when you sell your home,
and you're thinking, oh my
goodness, I leased this HVAC.
How can I transfer it?
Can I transfer it at all?
- Great question and the answer
is yes, you can transfer it,
and I think honestly,
any new homeowner that buys
your home is gonna be thankful
that they're just gonna go into a system
that they don't have to worry about,
because lots of people who buy homes,
sometimes it's their first home,
and they're not sure what to do.
With this, they don't have to do nothing.
- I love it, I love it.
I know that was definitely me
when I bought my first home.
All I wanted to do was turn the lights on,
have it be cool in the summer,
and hot in the winter, or at least warm.
Okay, so we got that covered.
Now do you have any type of specials
for our Great Day viewers?
Maybe you're interested and
you need a little push at home,
so we got the owner of Michael
and Son here, and I'm saying,
what do you have for
our homeowners watching?
- Well, I'll tell you this.
I don't want to sound too infomercially,
but I will say that I want you
guys to really get into this.
I want you to enjoy your summer,
and if you guys honestly,
call us and call us now,
we're gonna give you three,
the first three months
of payments are on me.
- I love that, I love it.
So the first three,
you don't even have to
talk to Basim himself,
just call, get the first
person who answers and says,
I saw Basim on Great Day and
you get the first three months.
- Yes.
- I'm repeating this now,
so people will call me,
you get the first three months on you.
- Absolutely, and if you
want, you can call me.
This is my personal
cellphone number right here.
No, it's not here.
I'm just joking.
- Okay, 866.
Okay, okay, but that's your number,
and I just so appreciate
you making it easy,
because no one really knows an HVAC system
unless you're an HVAC
expert, and that's you.
So I appreciate you coming here today.
- I appreciate you having me.
- And you did great
for live unexpected TV.
(laughing)
You did great.
- Thank you.
- Yeah okay, so remember for
the deal, you have to call,
so remember call about Michael
and Son's leasing options
and they're standing by to
take your calls right now.
That number is 866-214-8608,
or you can visit them
online at MichaelandSon.com,
now let's send it over to Howard
for an update on the weather.
- Yeah, you know Markette,
these batteries only last so long.
They're been on since 4:15 this morning,
but we're continuing to track the storms.
Heaviest stuff now is
pushing from D.C. south,
although we're not done with the rain,
but I think the heaviest
rains if you are north of D.C.
you probably have the
worst you're gonna see,
and there's plenty of
flooding going on right now.
Ellen's got some incredible pictures
she's gonna share in just a moment,
but on the doppler
you'll notice D.C. south
we're seeing the heaviest stuff.
Flood warnings now go into
Prince George's County
'til one o'clock in advance
of this mass of water
that is coming out of
the Alexandria, Clinton,
Upper Marlboro, the Southern
part of the District,
over toward even Northern Anne Arundel,
Northern Calvert and Southern
Anne Arundel Counties.
You see D.C. now, we're out of
the heaviest, heaviest stuff,
at least in the heart of downtown.
Alexandria down toward Mount Vernon,
Accokeek still getting pounded there
with just lighter, more
regular rains if you will,
back toward Georgetown, Northwest
D.C., Bethesda, Potomac.
West Springfield to Mount Vernon
as we said to Piscataway
in Prince George's County.
And the heavy rains have
made it to Brandywine,
it's gonna get a little bit heavier.
Waldorf, it'll be there in
the next 10 or 15 minutes,
and we'll give it another
10 or 15 minutes after that.
As this whole area's moving southeast
at about 25 miles a hour or so.
Charles County, eventually into Calvert
and St. Mary's as well,
and let's not forget west of the river.
Our friends in Prince William
not seeing it nearly as badly,
and I think that'll be
the same case in Stafford.
Some of these rain totals by the way,
that's close to five inches
in the last 12 hours.
These are 12 hour rain
totals in Frederick,
I saw a picture out of
Baker Park underwater.
We saw some areas north of Martinsburg,
five and a half inches
of rain since last night.
Adamstown had about four and a half,
four and three quarters since last night.
So we've had widespread
flooding, please be careful,
take all of these closed
roads very seriously.
What are we looking at
for the next 12 hours?
Well, still a chance for some rain
and showers I think
through early afternoon,
slip south and west, we dry out.
We see a little sun,
but a cooler day than we've seen in awhile
with highs in the lower 80s.
Ellen Brian, unbelievable.
- Howard.
- [Howard] You showed me
that map of the Beltway,
it's almost completely red.
- [Ellen] Oh yes, yeah.
I can go to that first
here, let's show you that.
The I-270 Southbound, the
Beltway, inner and outer loops,
especially over by the
American Legion Bridge,
because that is where we're seeing
that first traffic lane camera
that I'm showing you now.
We had a closure here.
No longer a closure,
but take a look at traffic
that is following that.
We had a tree that fell down
on a car, caused an accident,
so we're seeing these significant delays.
Plus the rain's delaying people.
Flooding on so many roads.
This is right here, Lee Highway
at North Kirkwood Street.
If you can look closely through,
I know the raindrops on that camera lens,
there are cars that have been
trapped in high water there.
We've also been getting
people on social media
sending us so many things,
including some flooding in Metro as well,
and the entrance that has
been blocked to the C&O Canal,
so we'll see.
Oh, we have Adam Longo first.
Okay, so Adam Longo,
he was up by Newcut Road
and 355, or Frederick Road.
Take a look at the flooding there.
There's that car.
- Clarksburg, Clarksburg area.
- [Ellen] It's in Clarksburg
area, Montgomery County.
That car that's over by the
guardrail as you're seeing that,
and Howard and I were talking about this.
You typically see this area
have that kind of high water.
- [Howard] Yeah, just
south of the middle school.
I live a mile or so north of there,
so this is a very low area on 355.
- [Ellen] Yeah, Adam's saying
the road's completely washed out.
Then we have trouble at the
Metro, take a look at this.
This is the Virginia Square Metro,
do you see the water that's rushing
right into the tracks from above?
It's just coming down.
This is from a viewer,
Nina Farah sent this in.
She said, "I think I'm
gonna be late to work,"
is what she said with this, I think so,
and she has many other tweets
that she's been sending out,
but water rushing in there,
and then also the C&O
Canal tweeted out this.
They said their Great Falls entrance,
the road there is completely closed.
They have trees that are down.
I've seen pictures of
high water there as well,
so we're seeing this all over.
You gotta be careful out there.
So many swift water rescues happening.
Be careful out there this morning.
We're gonna take a quick break,
then we'll come right back
here and continue our coverage.
(bright music)
- [Announcer] WUSA9
wants you to win tickets
to the UniverSoul Circus.
Don't miss your chance.
(energetic music)
Just text UNIVERSOUL to
65047 right now to win.
- We'll buy your house as
is and handle all repairs.
Get to life's next step
with peace of mind and
cash in your pocket.
♪ Express Homebuyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
- [Announcer] Right now,
join Planet Fitness for
$1 down, no commitment.
Or you can work out at home
in your spacious laundry/storage closet.
Or from the comfort of your own bedroom.
Or surrounded by the lights of your life.
(children shouting)
(dog barking)
Leave home at home, and
leave the gym to us.
Get a great workout with
treadmills, ellipticals,
weights, free fitness training and more.
Join Planet Fitness for $1 down,
$10 a month, no commitment.
Ends July 16th.
- Hey guys, what's going on?
So we are here at Salon Virage
with owner himself, Fadi,
and he is about to do a
step by step treatment
on his client called the scalp treatment,
so let's get started.
- So this is the phytopolleine here.
This is gonna balance your scalp.
We leave it 30 minutes and after that,
Pam will shampoo her hair.
(bright music)
- All right Fadi, we just did step one.
What's step two?
- So now we're gonna do a haircut.
It's gonna be bob
degrade, which is layers.
(bright music)
- All right Fadi, you
just finished step two,
so what's step three?
- Step three is look at the client,
and then see where it
needs the be texturized
and then fill in the gaps.
- Oh wow, this looks beautiful.
So if you guys need your hair done,
get down to Salon Virage,
visit them at salonvirage.com,
or you can call the number below.
- After my car accident,
I didn't know that a lawyer would help
deal with all my medical bills.
- I didn't know I could also get money
for pain and suffering.
- I didn't know the insurance company
wasn't going to give me
the settlement I deserved.
- We do know at Saiontz &
Kirk we know injury law,
and we know how to get you
the most money possible.
- Clients of Saiontz & Kirk
have collected over $1 billion.
- When you need a lawyer,
you have a lawyer.
- Call 1-800-LAWYERS or
visit YouHaveALawyer.com,
if you have a phone, you have a lawyer.
- The only thing that
I would do differently,
the only thing,
I should've called
Express Homebuyers sooner.
♪ Express Homebuyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
(energetic music)
- Well, welcome back to
Great Day Washington.
It's what everyone is
talking about this morning,
besides the storm, it's
the Women's World Cup.
The U.S. Women's Team is back on top
after beating the Netherlands
two to nothing yesterday in France.
It's the fourth World
Cup title for the U.S.
and the second in a row.
Let's go to the highlights.
Now the game went into half scoreless,
but in the second half,
who else but Megan Rapinoe
got the U.S. on board,
scoring easily on a penalty kick,
then about six minutes later,
Rose Lavelle scored a beautiful goal
to give the U.S. the two to nothing lead.
Lavelle plays for the Washington Spirit
in the National Women's Soccer League.
It was her third goal of the World Cup.
The goal also helped
the U.S. break a record
for most goals by one team
in a Women's World Cup,
with 26 goals.
And from there, the party was on.
Megan Rapinoe won the Golden Boot
for most goals in the World Cup.
She's just the second American
to ever win the award.
Her teammate Alex Morgan
won the Silver Boot for
the second most goals.
And you'll remember during the tournament,
Megan Rapinoe sparked some controversy
saying she and the team
would not visit the
White House if they won.
Right now it's unclear if
they'll even be invited,
but President Trump did tweet,
"Congratulations to the
U.S. Women's Soccer Team
"on winning the World Cup.
"Great and exciting play,
America is proud of you all."
But he stopped short of saying
if they'd be invited to the White House.
Well either way, we know
the team will be honored
with a ticker tape parade in
New York City on Wednesday.
One out of two isn't bad ether.
Earlier, we told you about
the U.S. Women's Team
winning the World Cup,
but the Men's Team wasn't
so lucky last night.
They lost one to nothing in
the Gold Cup Final in Chicago.
The Gold Cup features teams
from North America, Central
America, and the Caribbean.
The game was scoreless
until the 73rd minute
when Mexico's Jonathan Dos Santos
scored to give Mexico the lead.
This is Mexico's eighth
Gold Cup Championship.
Great Day Washington will
be right back after this.
- [Announcer] WUSA9
wants you to win tickets
to the UniverSoul Circus.
Don't miss your chance.
(energetic music)
Just text UNIVERSOUL to
65047 right now to win.
- [Announcer] Tuesday.
- Let's get this party started!
- [Announcer] The international sensation,
Love Island is coming to CBS.
So let's meet the ladies.
- I definitely keep boys on their toes.
- I'm Kyra, I can be a
little bit of a flirt.
- I'm really excited to be
here, excited for the men.
- [Alexandra] I am very romantic.
- They guys can't ghost me,
there's nowhere to hide.
- Kind of like a real live dating app.
- [Announcer] Love Island
with host Arielle Vandenberg.
Series premiere CBS Tuesday, 8/7 Central.
- [Announcer] For a limited
time ARS Rescue Rooter
will buy back your old
inefficient HVAC system
when we take up to $1500 off
your new heating and
cooling system purchase.
Visit ARSofVirginia.com.
♪ Call ARS and Rescue Rooter ♪
- Sterling Motorcars
is the premiere luxury
dealer in the Mid Atlantic.
Offering BMW, MINI, Rolls-Royce,
Lamborghini, and McLaren.
For the best luxury car buying experience,
come to Sterling Motorcars.
Creating sterling moments
one customer at a time.
- [Announcer] Update your floors
with Empire Today's $50 room sale.
But one room,
get floors for all other
rooms for just $50 each.
So, when you buy one room,
it's only $50 for laminate in the kitchen,
$50 for carpet in the bedroom,
and $50 for hardwood in the office.
There's no limit.
Buy one room,
and it's $50 for floors
in each additional room.
Schedule now.
♪ 800-588-2300 ♪
♪ Empire Today ♪
- Hi, my name is Jeffrey Tate,
and I have lost 78 pounds in 93 days
with Dr. Cory Aplin's weight loss program.
I have more energy now
than I've ever had before.
I can go back and wear my old clothing.
I no longer have any hypoglycemic
episodes like I once had.
- Hi, I'm Dr. Aplin.
To find out how you can lose
up to a pound of fat per day,
call this number right now
for your no obligation consultation.
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm Dan from MarketPro Homebuyers,
and we want to buy your home.
Don't make repairs, don't pay commissions.
For a no obligation
offer, call 301-799-7355
or visit marketprohomebuyers.com.
- [Announcer] Leaky faucets?
Clogged drains?
Schedule an appointment with
ARS Rescue Rooter today.
We'll even take $50 off.
ARS Rescue Rooter, making
it work, making it right.
Visit ARSofVirginia.com.
♪ Call ARS and Rescue Rooter ♪
(dramatic music)
- Welcome back, we want to update you
on what's going on with the
weather here this morning,
because we've had lots of
flooding across the region
from Frederick to Howard,
to Montgomery Counties, now into D.C.
And the heaviest rains are moving south
into Southern Prince
George's, Charles County,
eventually Calvert and St. Mary's.
I think Virginia, west of the Potomac,
not looking nearly as bad,
but we still have some rainfall rates
in Alexandria and Clinton,
over to Waldorf here, into
Northern Charles County.
Some of these rainfall rates
are three, four, five inches per hour.
That'd be the instantaneous rate,
but you're able to pick up
a quick one to two, three inches of rain,
and that's why we've
got the flash flooding
and all of these flash flood warnings.
You'll notice once we get to
Alexandria, north of there,
it's not as bad.
Still some moderate showers
across the eastern half of D.C.
with the heaviest stuff
south of Morningside.
We're gonna take awhile before
the water actually recedes.
So the heaviest rains now in
Vernon, Piscataway, Brandywine,
now down toward Waldorf
into Charles County.
Continuing to move to the southeast,
so our friends in Calvert,
Charles County, get ready.
The Charles and Prince George's warning,
the southern Prince George's,
that one goes until one
o'clock this afternoon.
The good news is, well, we've
had some rainfall rates,
or rainfall actually observed
over five inches in the last 12 hours,
the afternoon looks better.
We will dry out with highs in the low 80s.
Have a great Monday.
(energetic music)
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm Dan from MarketPro Homebuyers
and we want to buy your home.
Don't make repairs, don't pay commissions,
and don't wait another day.
We'll get you the cash you need.
No agent fees, no closing costs.
We'll even help you
pack and move for free.
For a no obligation
offer, call 301-799-SELL.
That's 301-799-7355 or visit
marketprohomebuyers.com.
We buy houses as is, on
your schedule, call today.
- Weather matters.
I'll have DC's most accurate
forecast tonight on WUSA9.
- Lola Carmichael, L.A.'s
newest Superior Court judge.
The state of California
versus Daphne Reavis.
Did you do what you're accused of?
- No.
- We're going to trial.
♪ You say I'm in love ♪
- If I'm going to take
away that girl's freedom,
I'd like to know if she's guilty first.
♪ And I believe ♪
- Up on that bench,
everything is different.
You try that again in a courtroom,
and I will make sure
you have nothing left
to serve and protect.
Thanks for coming.
- [Announcer] All Rise,
coming this fall to CBS.
- Okay, have fun at your dad's.
- Okay, love you, Mom.
- Bye.
- What do you think?
- I like it.
Come no, got him!
- Yes!
(clattering)
You hungry?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Bye Dad.
- Bye buddy.
- How was it?
- Dad's internet is amazing.
- Well, you know Mom's
cookies are also amazing.
That's what I thought.
- [Announcer] Get up to 1 GIG
speeds on the day you move in.
Cox internet starting at $29.99
per month for up to 10 MEGS.
- After my car accident,
I didn't know I could get money
for time I missed from work.
- I didn't know my case
could be settled without going to court.
- I didn't know the insurance company
would try to pay me as little as possible.
- We do know at Saiontz &
Kirk, we know injury law,
and we know how to get you
the most money possible.
- Days, nights, weekends,
call Saiontz & Kirk.
When you need a lawyer, you have a lawyer.
- Call 1-800-LAWYERS or
visit YouHaveALawyer.com,
if you have a phone, you have a lawyer.
- I didn't realize how bad my smile was
with fillings and root canals.
I had to do something.
I looked at partial bridges.
I looked at dentures.
Out of all the options,
ClearChoice was the only choice for me.
- [Announcer] At ClearChoice,
we bring hope to millions
who suffer from missing or failing teeth.
With dental implants that look, feel,
and function like strong natural teeth.
- All the specialists
with all the technology
they need all in one spot.
It makes delivering this 21st
century, world class dentistry
very easy to do and we do it in one day.
- [Ron] I can laugh, people
crack a joke and I smile,
it was a life changing thing.
- [Announcer] Call today to schedule
your free comprehensive consultation
and i-CAT 3D imaging scan.
We'll even talk financing
options while you're here.
- They not only helped
to rebuild my smile,
but helped me to rebuild
my self-confidence.
They really set me free.
I mean, look at this smile.
- [Announcer] At ClearChoice,
you're about to discover
what you've been missing all these years.
Call ClearChoice today.
- [Announcer] The CBS Evening News
with Norah O'Donnell beginning July 15th.