- [Announcer] Sales event!
Plus, get up to 125%
of GDB with Easy Trade.
Limited time savings are here
during our Presidents' Day sales event.
♪ Sheehy.com ♪
- Snow, ice and rain on the way!
- Delays throughout the day.
- [News Anchor] Good Morning
Washington, tomorrow!
- [TV Announcer] From Hollywood,
it's Jimmy Kimmel Live!
Tonight! (audience applauding)
Regina King!
From The Punisher, Jon Bernthal!
This week in Unnecessary Censorship,
and music from Juanes!
And now, in all sincerity, Jimmy Kimmel!
(orchestral music)
(audience applauding)
- Hi everybody, how're you doing?
I'm Jimmy, I'm the host of
the show, thank you very much!
(audience applauding)
Thanks for coming!
Thank you!
Welcome!
Welcome to Hollywood!
I appreciate that!
Hey I have a story,
so last night after the show
I hosted a concert, there was
a big concert at the Forum.
(audience cheering and applauding)
It was a tribute to the
late, great Chris Cornell,
were you there, is that
why you're yelling, okay!
(audience cheering)
The lineup was incredible,
it was Chris Stapleton,
Adam Levine, Metallica,
Miley Cyrus, Foo Fighters,
Audioslave, Soundgarden, amazing!
And you had fun, right Guillermo?
- A lot of fun!
- Guillermo had a lot of fun.
(Guillermo laughing heartily)
- Guillermo was like,
hey, are you going to that, it's like,
yeah, yeah come with me to the show
and Cleto went, and Dicky went,
Jeff our keyboard player went, a few guys.
At one point in the night,
I think it was two-thirds
of the way through the
show, I was on stage
and somebody yelled, where's Guillermo?
So I gave Guillermo a shout-out,
I said Guillermo is here,
and the whole Forum erupted in tears.
It was crazy, it was like, it
was about the same reaction
they gave Brad Pitt and so
then, (audience laughing)
I go backstage, I text
Guillermo 'cause I wanna,
kind of know what he thought,
and where were you when you
got the text I sent you?
- I was at home!
- He was at home, yeah.
(audience laughing heartily)
After Metallica he ditched us
and got in an Uber and went home. (laughs)
In fairness Guillermo has to go bed early
because he's gotta be at work at 2:00 p.m.
(audience laughing)
Today is day 27 of the government
shutdown which is nuts.
Remember when Trump said he'd run
the government like a business?
Turns out the business was Radio Shack!
(audience laughing and applauding)
Trump is--
(audience cheering)
Desperately--
(audience applauding)
Trying to pin blame for
this shutdown on Democrats,
he lashed out this morning.
He wrote, "The left has
become totally unhinged.
"They no care what right for our country!"
That's right, and you see how he spelled,
he's just as good at spelling country
as he is in running it, it's--
(audience laughing)
Most of Trump's hire is directed
at Nancy Pelosi, the Speaker of the House.
Yesterday Nancy Pelosi
sent the president a letter
suggesting he postpone his scheduled
State of the Union Address,
until the shutdown is over.
She will not permit him to give it
from the House of Representatives.
So today, Trump retaliated
with a letter of his own
informing Nancy Pelosi
that he was canceling
her flight to Afghanistan.
She's going there on a military aircraft,
and he told her, if she wants
to go she can fly commercial!
(audience laughing)
Into a war zone!
And, he sent the letter less an hour
before she was supposed to leave.
It was the presidential equivalent of,
you break up with me, I break up with you!
And I bet he was so delighted with himself
when he came up with this idea.
In fact an official from
the White House said,
he spent the day watching coverage of it
and was very pleased this afternoon.
But he may the only one who's pleased,
because even some of his
fellow Republicans said
this was a petty thing to do,
and all the Democrats are mad.
This is from CNN today,
reporter Phil Mattingly
stopped the House Majority
Leader Steny Hoyer, like this:
- We're really seeing--
- Hold on one second,
I'm sorry to interrupt, here's
the House Majority Leader
Steny Hoyer, talking
about what's going on--
- Okay, hold on a second,
because that is the most
threatening microphone
I think I've ever seen in my life!
(audience laughing and applauding)
Gimme your money old man!
Desperate times I guess!
You know, if the Democrats
can't convince Trump
to end this silly shutdown I
think I know somebody who can.
Lot of people would try
to make sense out of this
but the clearest voice I've
heard on the subject so far,
believe it or not, came from Cardi B.
- Hey y'all, I just wanna remind ya
because it's been a little
bit over three weeks okay?
It's been a little bit over three weeks.
Trump, is now ordering as his summonse,
federal government workers
to go back to work,
without getting paid.
Now, I don't wanna hear
ya (bleep) talkin' about,
oh, but Obama shut down
the government for 17 days,
yeah bitch!
For healthcare!
So your grandma could
check her blood pressure,
and you bitches could
go check your (bleep)
at the gynecologist with
no mother (bleep) problem!
(audience laughing and applauding)
- Cardi B is right!
(audience applauding)
Almost 800,000 federal
employees are not getting paid,
and every night until it's over
we're hiring a furloughed
worker per night.
Last night we brought in a NASA
engineer who was out of work
and now let's say hello to
our new employee tonight,
please welcome Andrew Rigopoulos!
Andrew, come on in here!
(audience cheering and applauding)
Welcome!
Thank you for coming!
- I'm here!
- So I see this!
Tell us what you do, specifically.
- I'm an engine station ranger
at Cabrillo National Monument
in San Diego--
- You are a ranger!
And so you work in, we still
have national parks correct?
- We do--
- That's a good sign, yeah?
- Well, if people over
visit 'em and damage 'em
then we won't have them anymore.
- And right now, there's nobody working
at the park you work at--
- No, we have a crew
of rangers that actually watch it
to make sure that our
resources aren't damaged
while we're there--
- You are considered
to be a non-essential government employee?
- Yeah, I stay home and
watch a lot of Netflix--
- Yeah, okay. (audience laughing)
Well you actually came up,
usually we come up with the job,
but you came up with an
idea for a job, that I like.
- Yeah, I pitched it to my
brother first and he said--
- What're you gonna do for us tonight?
- Since parks are important
and nature's important--
- Yes?
- I'm gonna take care
of our urban landscape
and water your plants.
- You're gonna water the plants here--
- Yeah--
- Now we don't have
that many plants.
- No.
- But if you see any, water 'em.
- Okay.
- Okay, thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- I appreciate it.
(audience cheering and applauding)
- So Andrew, oh, Andrew!
I forgot, we got you this!
So in case you don't you
have one of your own.
- Thank you--
- And by the way,
if you see any funny lookin' plants,
just ignore them okay?
- Okay.
- Thank you very much,
that's Andrew, Rigopoulos!
(audience cheering and applauding)
The president appears to
be on a collision course
with the law right now, his
alleged lawyer Rudy Giuliani
was back on CNN last night,
and rudier than ever.
He made a crazy appearance,
on Chris Cuomo's show.
This one, if we didn't have this on video
it would almost be too much to believe.
- The amount of false
reporting about this case,
is despicable!
- Mr. Mayor, false reporting--
- It's despicable--
- Is saying that nobody
in the campaign had any
contacts with Russia.
False reporting, is saying that there
has been no suggestion
of any kind of collusion
between the campaign and any Russians.
Because now you have Paul Manafort,
giving poll data--
- I never said--
- That winds up leading
to this coincidence--
- Well you just misstated my position.
I never said there was no
collusion between the campaign,
or between people in the campaign--
- Yes you have--
- I have no idea, I have not!
I said the president of the United States.
There is not a single bit of evidence
the president of the United States,
committed the only crime
you could commit here,
conspired with the
Russians to hack to DNC.
- (laughs) Wow, really!
Of course he never said it.
Nobody in the Trump
administration ever said
any of the things they
say all the time but--
(audience laughing) But there must be
another Rudy Giuliani out there
who's been going around
saying there was no collusion,
between Russia and the campaign.
- Is it still the position
of you and your client,
that there was no collusion
with the Russians whatsoever
on behalf of the Trump campaign?
- Correct.
So he did say it.
The surest sign of how deeply screwed up
this administration is,
is that Rudy Giuliani
is still allowed to go on
TV, to speak on their behalf.
(audience laughing) Go on, Rudy!
- The president did not--
- We said nobody had--
- With the Russians--
- Any contact, tons--
- Whatever collusion is--
- Of people are contacted.
Nobody colluded, the guy
running his campaign--
- He didn't say nobody--
- Was working on an issue--
- He said he didn't--
- At the same time as the convention.
- He said he didn't,
he didn't say, nobody.
How would you know, that
nobody in your campaign--
- He actually did say that, Rudy.
He said nobody--
- Well I never that--
- And then he said as far as I know--
- If he said that he said it in,
well as far as he knows that's true!
- Rudy Giuliani is like a
Choose Your Own Adventure!
It just changes! (audience laughing)
But the truth is it doesn't
matter what Rudy Giuliani says,
he's not the one being investigated yet!
But what matters is,
did the president say
there was no collusion
between the Russians and his campaign?
- There was no collusion between
the Trump campaign and the Russian people.
- Yeah, and at some point,
Rudy's gonna have to deny
that Trump is even the president.
But the important thing,
in Giuliani's mind
is that Robert Mueller
put this thing to rest.
- He puts out the report,
and then we get it
and we see what it has--
- Well let's--
- I've always seen this--
- Let's get it now--
- I've always seen this
as a false argument,
the idea of he's now
showing us what he has--
- Well let's do it--
- It's not over.
- Well let's do it.
- But he's gotta finish--
- It's over enough!
We've answered all those--
- What does that mean--
- Questions on collusion--
- Over enough?
- How much longer are you
gonna let him do this--
- He just put out that
your campaign chairman
was playing with the Russians!
- But we don't, that isn't what,
we don't need a special council
to investigate a campaign chairman.
- Oh boy, poor Rudy!
Someday he's gonna be in a mental facility
telling the nurses that he used
to be the mayor or New York
and they'll be like,
uh-huh! (audience laughing)
In the mean time, (audience applauding)
while that's goin' on
there, we have new details
about Trump's former
lawyer/friend Micheal Cohen.
According to the Wall Street Journal,
and according to Cohen
himself in a lead up
to Trump's run for president,
Cohen hired a company
to rig online polls in his favor.
You know these polls that you go on
and click which thing you want?
But Cohen says, the president directed him
to juice two polls, a CNBC poll
of America's top business
leaders, and a Drudge Report poll
of Republican candidates for president.
Even those didn't work out.
Not only did he not win
either of the polls,
I think he didn't even crack
the top 100 in the CNBC one.
The guy Cohen hired to do
this, according to The Journal
showed up at Trump Tower,
looking for $50,000 he was owed
and when he did, the
report says Cohen gave him
a Walmart bag with 12 to $13,000 in cash
and a boxing glove he
claimed had been worn
by a Brazilian MMA fighter as payment.
It's like a scene out of the
world's dumbest heist movie,
(audience laughing)
it's Ocean's Chapter 11.
And so, the goon Cohen hired is an IT guy,
he's got a company, his
name is John Gauger.
There's not much about him online,
but this audition tape he
made trying to get on Survivor
in 2005 kind of tells
you all you need to know.
- In my line of business
I deal with people
from around the globe on a daily basis.
This has given the uncanny
ability to make anybody like me.
This will allow me to be
the most loved Survivor
contestant of all times,
and maybe the most hated too.
- Only the best people, you know?
Literally everyone around Trump
is a character from a reality show,
and that is not even the
best part of the story.
So Cohen also asked the
guy, while he was doin' this
to set up a Twitter account
called Women for Cohen.
This is a real account,
was created back in 2016,
it's for quote, "Women who
love and support Michael Cohen.
"Strong, pit bull, sex
symbol, no nonsense."
Basically Cohen asked this
guy, help me rig the election.
Hey, while you're at it,
could you make people
think girls like me too?
(audience laughing) Because I loved this
I clicked to see who was
following this account,
and some of the women for
Cohen are named John, Ted,
Elvis, Theodore, Kevin and Sonny.
We also have Steve, Douglas, Aaron,
Casillas, Chris and Bill.
And these are some of
the things they tweeted.
Put that up on the screen.
Snazzy looking & ready to
#MAGA. (audience laughing)
Best looking men award goes to,
heart and emoji, we love you guys!
This has gotta be the saddest thing
I ever heard of in my whole life.
We're like a wee away from finding out
Michael Cohen had a burner phone
he used to send dirty texts to
himself! (audience laughing)
I may have underestimated Michael,
'cause he might be a lot more hilarious
than I ever imagined!
Hey by the way, I don't
know if you heard about this
but YouTube is, you familiar with YouTube?
Yeah, okay, YouTube is
cracking down on fun.
YouTube announced that they're
banning dangerous pranks
and challenges from their platform.
They posted this.
"Dangerous Challenges and
Pranks Enforcement Update.
"Hi everybody, YouTube is home
"to many beloved viral
challenges and pranks,
"like Jimmy Kimmel's Terrible
Christmas Presents prank"
thank you, "or the water
bottle flip challenge.
"That said, we've always
had policies to make sure
"what's funny doesn't cross the line
"into being harmful or dangerous.
"Our community guidelines
prohibit content"
blah, blah, blah, "dangerous activities"
all this kind of stuff.
Basically YouTube has just
banned YouTube videos.
And (audience laughing) I have to say
someone that loves a good
prank and likes to do them,
I think it's sad that a few bad apples
had to ruin the fun of eating
poisonous detergent packets
for everyone but, (audience
laughing) the bigger question is
how do you know before you do something
what qualifies as
dangerous and what doesn't?
I mean we've done some stuff that
could potentially go in
a dangerous direction.
So anyway, YouTube
happens to have an office
right next door to us
so we called over there
and I went over to their office,
to run some ideas by their
content standards executive.
Hi there--
- Hi!
- How are ya?
- Good, how are you?
- Thanks for having me.
- Of course--
- Appreciate it.
So I was reading about these new rules
that you guys have--
- Yes.
- With the YouTube challenges.
And I'm a little bit concerned about it
because we do a lot of that
kind of stuff on the show.
- Well I mean we trust what you do,
that's a different situation--
- Well that's great news.
So I can do anything?
- Well I wouldn't say anything,
but I think--
- Okay, well let me--
- I think usually--
- Let me run some things
by you and you can just tell me,
because there are things we're working on
and I don't wanna get
into it, and you know.
Okay, the I bet you can't
eat all the knives challenge.
- (audience laughing) Well,
no I would say not that one.
- Really, that's a no?
- Not that one.
- The setting my brother
on fire challenge.
- (audience laughing)
That sounds dangerous, no.
- Dad, I boiled the toaster challenge.
- No--
- While it's plugged in.
- N-no.
- The ghost pepper up the butt challenge?
- (audience laughing) Nope!
- The blindfolded crossbow challenge.
- No.
- The jump the zoo
fence challenge, people jump
over the fence at the zoo
and get in with the animals--
- Not that, no--
- All right, asbestos to
baby powder challenge?
- Definitely no.
- Let's make friends on
Craigslist challenge.
(audience laughing) That one's okay?
All right, can I borrow
your pencil for a second?
Thank you very much--
- Well, we would need to,
it couldn't just be--
- Okay, there you go!
Seat belts are for snowflakes challenge.
- Uh, no! (audience laughing)
- Drunk unicycle challenge.
- No.
- I believe I can actually fly challenge,
is where somebody would
go out on a building
or out a window, whatever
and R. Kelly style,
but not that R. Kelly style,
the other R. Kelly style.
- No, on every level, no--
- The boiling water bucket challenge,
this would be for charity.
Like the ice bucket challenge but hotter.
- No.
- Borrow cop's gun challenge?
- Nope.
- Grandma's been missing
for eight weeks challenge.
- No.
- What if we wanna find her?
We're helping to find her?
- Hey, I feel like we're starting up--
- What if she's in the trunk of a car?
- That's a pretty dark place--
- One more, I framed my mom
for drug trafficking challenge.
- (audience laughing) You know
what, I'm gonna take this.
- This is bull (bleep)
- We like the other stuff!
Oh, cap. (audience laughing)
- Now maybe I'll start my own YouTube.
(audience cheering and applauding)
MeTube!
We have a great show for you tonight!
We have music from Juanes,
Jon Bernthal is here,
and we'll be right back with Regina King!
(audience cheering and applauding)
(lively jazz music)
- [TV Announcer] ABC's Jimmy Kimmel Live!
Brought to you by T-Mobile!
♪ La la la ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ Drive house ♪
♪ Go back to wasting days ♪
- [TV Announcer] T-Mobile
will do the math for you.
Right now, when you join T-Mobile,
you get two lines of unlimited,
with two of the latest phones included
for just 100 bucks a month! (phone jingle)
- [TV Announcer] On March 1,
Madea's time comes to an end.
- Oh hell, now!
I'm a real thug, I'm a old G-M-A-D-E-A.
- [TV Announcer] From Tyler Perry!
- Your daddy's dead, and I'll
be coordinating the funeral.
- That funeral's gonna be messed up!
- [TV Announcer] Get ready!
- What the hell is you doin'?
- I never thought I'd die like this.
I thought I'd die in a strip club.
- [TV Announcer] For a
funeral that's to die for!
- (woman wailing) And look
at him, lying there dead,
didn't need no poll, we still alive.
- Bacon ain't never hurt nobody!
- [TV Announcer] A Madea Family Funeral.
Rated PG-13.
In theaters March 1.
- [TV Announcer] Tom and Tina
will watch their son take his first steps
on the living room floor
of their dream home.
But first, a few things must happen.
To start, they must grow tired
of their living situation.
So Tom will improve his credit.
Tina will negotiate a pay raise.
They'll bag lunch, shop generic,
limit their dumb purchases,
then use Credit Karma
to budget for a house.
Then six hours into moving
they'll christen their
home in the downstairs den,
next to a photo of Tina's father, Jerry.
Several months later, with
the help of Credit Karma,
well, here's to progress.
(techno music)
- [TV Announcer] Ashley HomeStore's
President's Day mattress
sale is in it's final week.
Save up to $500 on select Serta iComfort
adjustable mattress sets,
or get 0% interest for eight years
starting at just $25 a month.
Only at Ashley HomeStore.
(classical music)
- [TV Announcer] Only
Tylenol Rapid Release Gels
have laser drilled holes.
They release medicine
fast, for fast pain relief.
Tylenol.
(electronic music)
♪ Turn on the lights ♪
♪ We shall write in the dark ♪
- Almost time for me to go.
- Well, what if I--
- Drove me home?
- What if we lost track of time?
(adventurous music)
- What if we took a leap of faith?
(excited screaming)
(water splashing)
- What if you--
- Missed my flight next week?
♪ Come down from the mountain ♪
- [TV Announcer] The only RAV4.
♪ You have been strong ♪
Toyota.
Let's go places.
- [TV Announcer] Lady
Gaga and Bradley Cooper
perform together live on the Oscars,
ABC, Sunday.
- [TV Announcer] You've gotta
get to Checkers and Rally's.
Four items for just four bucks?
Nobody can beat that!
Get a Checker burger, a
spicy chicken sandwich,
or a crispy fish sandwich.
Fries, pie, and a drink for four bucks!
The four for four deal!
Checkers and Rally's.
Fast foodies know the deal.
- This is a commercial about buying cars.
That's a car, this is a phone,
and this is DriveTime!
- Cool.
- Need to get a car with your tax refund?
- OMG do I, but wait!
Where is the all the sexy
shots of cars driving
on city streets with no traffic?
- We don't need 'em!
99% of people who apply get approved!
It takes two minutes, and
you can do it from anywhere.
All you need is your phone.
- Whaaat?
- Yeeep!
Down payments with DriveTime
are $1,000 less on average,
so that tax refund can go a lot further.
- Holy Moly, that is a low down payment.
- Go to drivetime.com and see how much car
you can get with your
refund, in two minutes.
DriveTime. Genius!
- [TV Announcer] Get ready to crave
Checkers and Rally's, because
Texas toast garlic bread
covered in crispy onions and
sweet, smoky barbeque sauce.
You've just won at eating for only $2.99.
New Texas toast garlic bread doubles.
Checkers and Rally's.
Fast foodies know the deal.
(audience cheering and applauding)
(rock music)
- Hi.
And tonight, you know him
from Marvel's The Punisher on Netflix.
The Punisher, Jon Bernthal
is is here with us tonight.
(audience cheering and applauding)
This is a song, it's
called LaPlata Juanes,
from the Mercedes-Benz Stadium.
Next week,
we have new shows.
Chris Pine will be here,
Nathan Fillion, Dr. Phil,
from Game of Thrones, Lena
Headey, comedian Kellen Erskine
will be here, we'll have music
from Black and Flipton here
and on Monday, it's a big lead
day for America, on Monday,
it'll be two years since
our president took office
and we will salute and pay
tribute to this great man
with a star-studded mac extravaganza.
It's Jimmy Kimmel Live,
intermission accomplished
a half-time tribute to Trump,
and you're all invited,
that I can tell you.
That's Monday night. (audience
applauding and cheering)
Our first guest tonight is
a very talented actress,
with three Emmys and a
shiny new Golden Globe
and Critic's Choice Award to prove it,
If Beale Street Could
Talk, it's her movie,
it's in theaters now,
please welcome Regina King!
(audience cheering and applauding)
(exciting fast-paced music)
Congratulations,
on so many awards.
You are a fantastic actress.
- Thank you--
- There's no doubt about
that, and I will tell You--
(audience cheering and applauding)
Every time I see you on something,
my wife and I, we have a conversation
about what a great actress you are.
- Oh, thank you!
- How many awards have you
won for this movie so far?
Do you have any idea what the number is,
'cause I have a list.
- Do you really?
- Yes I do.
This is the list--
- Oh, my goodness--
- It's a long list, Golden
Globes, Critic's Choice,
I mentioned Austin Film Critics,
Boston Online Film Critics Association,
Boston Society of Film Critics.
- It's a lot.
- Indiana, Iowa, Las Vegas, Oklahoma,
The Online Film Critics
Society. (audience cheering)
Every city you can imagine,
the Satellite Awards,
do you even know about some of these?
- No!
- No.
- No, I mean I know about
them when they happen
but this whole award season
thing, it's been quite,
it's been an education, I have--
- In what way has it been an education?
- Because, well first of all
I didn't realize there were
so many different film critics
circle association reviews
and all of that.
- Right.
- Had no idea, kind of just thought,
the film critics, they're the
critics, they're the crew,
they're all together--
- They're one mass.
- Yeah!
- Yes.
- But, I mean--
- No.
- So I'm like, the Rancho
Cucamonga film critics,
review is gonna happen.
Every so often I get a call from my team
and I'm just tickled and
amazed because I don't know
about some of them but
I'm like, thank you!
- I know at this point
you probably have to give
some of them away to
neighbors or something right?
- Nooooo!
- Because you're--
- They're mine! (audience laughing)
My name--
- You're gonna keep
all of them--
- And I'm gonna keep them all!
- Even the Oklahoma Film Critics Circle?
- Even, because that one is, Oklahoma?
- That's the one, yeah! (laughs)
- Never would've saw that one coming!
- Are there enough film
critics in Oklahoma,
to form a circle? (audience applauding)
- I'm sure there are about eight.
- They're are probably--
- Yeah, at least.
- Well congratulations either way.
- Thank you.
- Do you run out of speeches?
Do you run out of things to say?
- I hope not, because I hope to be able
to continue to do work
that receives accolades,
but I just say a prayer,
and just make, please,
just don't let me slub,
or say something silly--
- Do you plan it out
beforehand, do you write something down
before you go--
- I don't, I feel like
that's jinxin' the whole thing.
- Interesting,
I think that's true, yes.
- Yeah, because--
- 'Cause there's nothin' more embarrassing
then gettin' home that night--
- And look at that paper,
and you're go like, yeah--
- And you go like, oh.
- Yeah, it's preparing for failure.
- Yeah, and the only thing about that is
there's always someone that you forget.
- Yes, right, you have to
remember everyone's name or else--
- Or you get names wrong.
- Oh, have you done that?
- I did.
- Do you think you need to thank anyone
who's name you don't
know how to pronounce?
(audience laughing)
- I say call them by their first name.
- I say that--
- Just 'cause usually
the last names are the doozies.
But I say just the first name.
- That's very, but most people
don't have this problem.
- They call them
champaign problems, right?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Okay.
- By the way happy birthday,
I know it was your birthday on Tuesday,
I saw--
- Thank you!
(audience cheering and applauding)
- Did they give you awards for that too,
or did you get gifts, or what did you do
for your birthday--
- I did, I did!
I got a lotta liquor!
- You did?
Yeah, I don't know what
that says about me, but--
- People give you bottles?
- Yes.
- Yeah, interesting.
- Nice bottles.
- And then when they give to you
do you open it up right away, and enjoy?
- No, I take my time--
- You take your time.
- I like to open them up with people.
- Did you have a party or anything?
- I did not have a party,
I had a party of one at the
spa, for about four hours.
It was so sweet because my masseuse,
she was walking me and she goes,
"I know I'm not supposed to say this,
"but I'm just so happy for you!"
- Oh really?
- And it was just so,
the amount of love that
I'm getting from people--
- Well you thank your
masseuse at the Oscars!
(audience laughing)
Do you remember her first name?
- No! (Jimmy laughs)
- I wanna thank Miranda
for the deep tissue.
- Yes, yes! (audience laughing)
You really got up in those shoulders!
- You might run out of people to thank
with all these awards, it's crazy!
- I don't think I'll run
out of people to thank--
- Who were you excited to
meet at the Golden Globes?
Is there anyone you had not met
or are these the same
people every single time?
- Okay, here's the thing.
This whole award season thing,
you're seeing a lot of the same people
and then you also see people
that you're a huge fan of,
and I normally don't up to people
and ask to take pictures,
just because I feel like
if they're not very nice people
then they've just destroyed
what's in my head--
- They'll ruin it for you--
- So, I decided to go against everything
that I know when I saw Sam Elliott.
- Sam Elliott, yeah!
Oh, you love Sam Elliott!
(audience laughing)
- Can you tell?
- Yeah, Sam Elliott's a real sex symbol,
kind of an under the radar sex symbol.
- Oh my God, I love that man!
- Did you tell him that?
- I did!
- Was he delighted?
- I did, he was just so
charming and so wonderful,
and even better than I had hoped
that he would be in the moment,
and the mustache is real!
- Oh yeah!
- It's just like, it's perfect!
And I just said, I love Roadhouse!
(audience laughing)
- That's the one huh?
- My sister and I used to watch Roadhouse,
oh my God!
- How old were you?
- I don't know, way too young to--
- To be watching Roadhouse.
- To have the thoughts
that I had about Sam Elliott--
- Oh, wow!
- But--
- So it looks like Sam
won a little somethin' too then.
When we come back, we're gonna
see a clip from your movie.
The movie is called, If
Beale Street Could Talk,
it is in theaters now,
Regina King is with us!
(audience applauding) We'll be right back!
(rock music)
- So cute--
- Best buds.
- Wait, who's lured out
there in the background?
- Did you--
- Boca, my child?
- That's totally unintentional--
- Why do you hate Jacob?
- What?
No, look, I can, un-Boca, see?
Boca, un-Boca.
- Wow.
(quiet whistling)
What kind of person, Boca's a child.
- I would never Boca your child.
Just so you know.
- [TV Announcer] Ashley
Homestore's President's Day
mattress sale is in it's final week!
Save up to $500 on select Serta iComfort
adjustable mattress sets!
Or get 0% interest for eight years
starting at just $25 a month,
only at Ashley HomeStore.
- I had a few good tricks to
help hide my bladder leak pad.
Like the old tunic tuck.
But Always Discreet is less bulky,
and it really protects,
'cause it turns liquid to gel.
So I have nothing to hide.
Always Discreet.
♪ Havana, oooh, mama ♪
♪ Half of my my heart is ♪
(cupcake splattering)
(dinging)
(jazz music)
- [TV Announcer] The verdict is in.
Audiences are giving
Fighting with my Family an A.
- I love that, say something else.
- [TV Announcer] And
America's top critics agree!
Calling it the first
truly great movie of 2019.
- Ding, ding, ding, bingo guys!
That's a big play to yes!
- [TV Announcer] Fighting with my Family.
Rated PG-13.
- [TV Announcer] Chili's three for 10
presents our signature sirloin steak.
Aged to perfection,
and served with a starter
and drink for just $10.
Out with the cousins,
and aunt Nancy,
who is politely described
as a free spirit!
Together, we Chili's.
(upbeat jazz music)
- You're going to Hollywood!
- Pain wants to stop you.
Block you.
Like that's gonna happen.
Icy Hot.
Icy to dull, hot to relax.
Rise from pain. (swishing)
(audience applauding)
Icy Hot.
- I just checked my credit.
- Checkin' hurts it you know.
- A lot of people say
that checking your credit can hurt it.
That's like believing that it takes
me seven years to digest.
It's just not true.
Adios! Oooohhhh!
- [TV Announcer] Check
your credit for free
now at Credit Karma.
Here's to progress.
(shopping carts clanging)
- A pain cream!
Honey you smell just
like my Walter used to.
- [TV Announcer] Don't smell like Walter!
Aspercreme is odor-free.
For maximum pain relief,
without that Walter smell.
Aspercreme!
No pain, no odor.
- As a fitness junkie,
I customize everything.
Bike,
wheels,
saddle,
that's why I switched to Liberty Mutual.
They customize my insurance
so I only pay for what I need.
I insured my car, and my bike.
My calves are custom too,
but I can't insure those.
Which is a crying shame.
- [TV Announcer] Only
pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, liberty, liberty ♪
♪ Liberty ♪
- I had this chest cold but
my medicine kept wearing off.
(coughing) Ahh!
- I missed you!
- Then I discovered Mucinex.
One pill lasts 12 hours, and I'm good.
- [TV Announcer] Mucinex releases fast
and lasts 12 hours, not four.
Let's end this.
(inspirational music)
- [TV Announcer] Zero to 60,
and everything in-between.
A vibrant collection of
cultures and activities await,
in greater Fort Lauderdale.
Start planning at sunny.org/letsgo.
- Does your customers
connecting to the Wi-Fi
ever slow down your business?
- Yes, it does slow things down.
- Aggravating.
- It's a nightmare.
- So our gig speed network is fast,
and we go beyond fast by making it easy
to create separate
networks for your business
and your customers, and even control
how much bandwidth each of those get.
So your business won't miss a beat.
- This is a big game changer.
- This is the new wave,
and whoever doesn't get on,
I think they would be left behind.
- [TV Announcer] Wi-Fi Pro
runs on the gate speed network.
Page is $49.95 a month for fast internet
and get a $300 prepaid card.
Comcast Business.
Beyond fast.
(telephone ringing)
- Remember the way we used to do things?
- Hey man!
- Like connect with friends.
- Dig it.
- Or get in shape.
Or sell a house,
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
(window breaking)
At Redfin we charge you a 1% listing fee.
And because redfin.com
is America's number one brokerage site,
our agents get more eyes on your home.
So you sell for thousands
more, than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin agent.
(inspirational music)
- [TV Announcer] New experiences.
Always on the menu.
A vibrant collection of
cultures and activities await,
in greater Fort Lauderdale.
Start planning at sunny.org/letsgo.
- [TV Announcer] America's
million dollar bed bug lawyer.
Thursday at 11:00 p.m.
- A child, is comin?
He's your grandchild.
I don't understand you,
it's your grandchild.
What difference does it
make how he gets here?
The child ain't got
nothin' to do with that.
Ain't non of us got
nothin' to do with that!
- That is Regina King
in (audience applauding)
If Beale Street could talk
and it's in theaters now.
This is a movie directed and
written by Barry Jenkins--
- Yes.
- Who did Moonlight,
and obviously won the
Academy Award for that.
When you're playing a mom in
the 70s, do you get excited
about the hairstyle,
'cause there are many--
- There are many--
- Ways you could go with that.
- There's a lot of ways to go.
I do and it's so interesting,
because there's a whole story
and I hope I can get it all in.
I wanted like an Afro--
- That's what I would have too.
- And Barry's like, "Yeah, no."
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, yeah!
- Why no?
- And was like, but you know
I'm no longer doing anything
like pressing my hair out.
I've got an Afro Barry,
that the world wants to see.
(audience laughing)
But he was like, "I
appreciate that, but no."
- No Afro--
- And so,
he really started sending pictures
of women that he felt visually,
Sharon is the role that I
play, would be, and I got it.
It made sense, and him
sharing that just turned into,
it made me understand the character--
- It started with the hair, and then--
- It started with the hair.
- Yeah, that's something else.
- Worked our way on down.
- I wanna ask you about something
you probably can't talk about at all,
which is Watchmen on HBO.
This is a show loosely based,
and we don't really know exactly--
- Exactly what it's based on--
- What it is, but you did
The Leftovers with Damon Lindelof--
- Yes--
- And that's a fantastic show,
and Damon is now running this
show, and writing this show,
are you the only person from The Leftovers
that he took with him to Watchmen?
- Well--
- Yeah!
- Yes.
- What can you tell us
about what you're up to on that show?
Anything?
Can you tell us which character you play?
- I can tell you, that I'm a woman.
- Okay?
(audience cheering)
- And that
I am maybe
somewhat of a badass?
- Okay.
- And I
may
have some scenes
with some really awesome actors.
(audience laughing)
- That's it huh?
Can you tell us anything
about the story
and in what era it will take place?
Sorry, this is real nerd stuff
and I need to get to the bottom of it.
- No, 'cause the fans are real.
If I just say the wrong bit of anything--
- That's what I'm hoping--
- They will crack--
- You're gonna do--
- The code and yeah--
You're trying to bait me--
- Yeah--
- Not gonna happen--
- No?
- No! (Jimmy laughs)
It's not gonna happen, not on my watch!
(audience applauding)
- Nicely done.
Regina King, If Beale Street Could Talk
is in theaters now.
(audience applauding)
Jon Bernthal is here, we'll be right back.
(upbeat jazz music)
♪ Que sera, sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be, will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera, sera ♪
♪ What will be, will be ♪
♪ Whatever will be, will be ♪
♪ Que sera, sera ♪
- Son, legends tell of a hidden world.
Home of the dragon.
It's your destiny to protect it.
(exciting adventurous music)
- It's you and me bud, always!
- [TV Announcer] Rated PG.
(crowd)
- [TV Announcer] The only
thing better than this bourbon,
are the friends you share it with.
(jazzy blues music)
Jim Beam Black.
- Why I shop Marshalls?
Because.
- Their prices will tell you.
(young girl cheering)
- The brands will surprise you.
- And every trip feels
like an instant victory.
- [Woman] Marshalls.
Never boring.
Always surprising.
- I am totally blind.
And Non-24 can me show up
too early, or too late,
or make me feel like I'm not really there.
Talk to your doctor,
and call 844-234-2424.
- When I became mice worry monster,
we'd stay up all night worrying.
But now he's healthy, drinks Pom
and doesn't worry about anything anymore.
Watch.
Karen's got the password
to your phone Mike.
She knows, Mike.
Nothing.
- I hear it in the back,
and she's watchin' it too.
Saying--
- What?
- And this what--
- [Man] I'll see you next week.
(mysterious music)
- [Woman] I've never seen that before.
(exhilarating music)
- (birds chirping) Wow!
That's an aggressive yellow!
- Pretty great huh?
- If you're a banana.
- I find it very appealing.
- [TV Announcer] Kellogg's
Raisin Bran with bananas!
Two scoops meet real banana slices.
- [Man] Done a good job raisin' ya.
- [TV Announcer] This is the Averys.
This is the Averys trying
the hottest new bistro.
Wait, and the hottest taqueria?
And the hottest, what are those?
Oh, pierogis! (drumbeat)
And this is the Averys
wondering if eating out,
is eating in to saving
for their first home.
This is JC.
- Welcome to Wells Fargo, how may I help?
- [TV Announcer] Who's here to help
the free financial health conversation.
No strings attached.
This is the Averys with the support
they needed to get back on track.
Well done guys!
- This is Wells Fargo.
- [TV Announcer] Before
discovering Nexium 24-hour
to treat his frequent heartburn,
Steven could only imagine
enjoying a spicy taco.
Now, his world explodes with flavor.
Nexium 24-hour stops acid
before it starts, for all
day, all night protection.
Can you imagine 24
hours without heartburn?
- How do we tell people,
they get the best of
both worlds with Sprint?
- How about we get
two-sport legend Bo Jackson?
- What's up?
- Oh.
- Guys, you don't need me!
Just tell people they get a great network,
and a great price with Sprint.
- Yes!
You can get an unlimited plan
and an iconic phone for just $25 a month.
On an LTE advance network,
that's up to two times faster than before.
- Bo does know.
- [TV Announcer] Switch to Sprint and get
an unlimited plan with the
Samsung Galaxy S9 lease
and Hulu included for just $25 a month,
no trade-in required.
(exciting fast-paced music)
- Agents, days of rivalry are over.
- We are working together.
- As a team.
(suspenseful music)
- Led by me.
- My charm is like a virus,
and before you know it,
boom, you're infected!
- Heart pass!
- [Man] You and I are
going to be attached.
- Seriously?
I'm holding a gun.
Ground rules, I don't do PDA.
- You gotta hold my hand.
- Not unless you want me to break it.
(intense music)
- [TV Announcer] Whiskey Cavalier.
Special sneak preview after the Oscars.
Series premieres February 27th on ABC.
- [TV Announcer] See.
Feel.
Climb.
First out, last in.
Look around corners.
Look in crannies.
Go down dark alleys.
Lose yourself.
Catch a lift.
Push boundaries.
Go walkabout.
Get set.
Go off to the goosebumps.
Never stop discovering.
The Land Rover Discovery
and Discovery Sport.
The only adventure sales
event is happening now.
Land Rover.
Above and beyond.
- [TV Announcer] Get ready to
crave Checkers and Rally's.
Because, Texas toast garlic bread.
Four of the greatest words ever.
Put that toast on two juicy patties,
with all the fixins for a classic double.
Or, cover it with crispy onions,
dripping with sweet, smoky barbeque,
then drop the garlicky, buttery mic.
Because you just won at
eating for only $2.99.
New Texas toast garlic bread double.
Checkers and Rally's.
Fast foodies know the deal.
- Welcome back with Jon Bernthal
and music from Juanes is coming,
but first, before we forge ahead
it's Thursday night which
means it's time to bleep
and blur the big TV moments of the week.
It is this week in Unnecessary Censorship.
(audience applauding)
- Britain's Prime Minister
Theresa May (bleep)
the biggest (bleep) in
our generation last night.
- My wife and I were
sort of looking forward
to a bit of respite and I
didn't wanna stick my (bleep)
into that meat grinder.
(audience laughing)
- Adding to the circumstances,
he keeps (bleep)
with Putin, he (bleep) the
interpreter's (bleep)--
- Who?
- He won't talk to--
- (bleep) Putin twice--
- The president, no he's
(bleep several times--
- Does anybody here not
(bleep) their children?
Wow, that's a lot of people.
(audience mildly laughing)
Not one?
- Remember two things.
Number one, please (bleep) my (bleep).
Number two, I'm probably (bleep).
- I was the last one (bleep) them today,
and now I am the first one
that (bleep) them tonight.
So, it felt really good.
- So I went down, to the
ground, and (bleep) my dog.
(audience laughing)
- Carolyn, that is not true.
- Don't interrupt.
- I remember my first time babysitting.
A four-year old locked me in the bathroom
and the fire department had to come.
- (mild laughing) My first time,
the (bleep) so far up his
(bleep) he wound up in the ER.
- Well hey, hey, hey! (audience
laughing and applauding)
Come on, let's go!
A little farther!
Let's go, let's go! (screams)
(audience laughing)
- We'll be right back with Jon Bernthal!
(heavy metal music)
- [TV Announcer] You
could take the treatment
of your ulcerative colitis,
in a a different direction.
Talk to your doctor
about Xeljanz.
A pill, not an injection or infusion.
For adults with moderate to
severe ulcerative colitis,
Xeljanz is the first and only
FDA approved pill for
moderate to severe UC.
It can reduce symptoms
in as early as two weeks.
Improve the appearance
of the intestinal lining,
and provide lasting
steroid-free remission.
Xeljanz can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes
fatal infections and cancers
including lymphoma have happened,
as have tears in the
stomach or intestines.
Serious allergic reactions,
low blood cell counts,
higher liver tests and cholesterol levels.
Don't start Xeljanz if
you have an infection.
Your doctor should perform blood tests
before and while taking Xeljanz,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor
if you're been somewhere
fungal infections are common,
and if you've had TB, hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
You could take your UC treatment
in a different direction.
Ask your gastroenterologist about Xeljanz.
- [TV Announcer] You haven't seen the sun
in like forever, so you
search for a beach vacation.
Sunny beaches, sandy beaches,
big beaches, small beaches,
until you're lost
searching for surfing dogs.
Then, you find VRBO, and
they search millions of homes
to find you the perfect beach house,
where you all find your own rooms,
and a grill bigger than
your kitchen back home.
And finding out about the
girl he likes at school
warms your heart even more than the sun.
From beach houses, to cabins, to condos.
Find vacation homes that
match you, with VRBO.
- Sometimes the best time, is
time you make for yourself.
Aveeno daily moisturizing lotion
improves skin hydration in just one day.
And for twice the moisture,
try the body wash too.
Aveeno, naturally beautiful results.
- [TV Announcer] This is 30 calories.
This is 30 calories.
This is not going to cut it.
This will.
V8.
V is for vegetables. (clinking)
Drink some.
(techno music)
♪ Turn on the lights ♪
♪ We shall write in the dark ♪
(electronic music)
- [TV Announcer] Tom and Tina
will watch their son take his first steps
on the living room floor
of their dream home.
But first, a few things must happen.
To start, they must grow tired
of their living situation.
So Tom will improve his credit.
Tina will negotiate a pay raise.
They'll bag lunch, shop generic,
limit their dumb purchases,
then use Credit Karma
to budget for a house.
And six hours into moving,
they'll christen their home
in the downstairs next to a
photo of Tina's father, Jerry.
Several months later, with
the help of Credit Karma,
well, here's to progress.
- [TV Announcer] Clean up
your family's trash talk.
With the Glad advanced
protection kitchen bag.
It's Glad's strongest, (intense music)
toughest,
most leak-resistant bag.
Be happy, it's Glad.
- [TV Announcer] From the start,
the C-Class was ahead of its time.
Still, we never stopped
making it stronger,
faster,
smarter.
Because to be the best,
is to never, ever, stop making it better.
(exhilarating music)
The new 2019 C-Class family.
Lease the 300 Sport Sedan for $429 a month
at your local Mercedes Benz dealer.
Mercedes Benz.
The best, or nothing.
- [TV Announcer] Now
you can make any morning
of the week, feel like the
weekend. (harmonica music)
With Jimmy Dean Simple Scrambles!
Made fresh with two real
eggs, sausage and cheese.
And ready in seconds!
- [Man] Why don't you put
a Sunday mornin' shine
on tomorrow morning's breakfast?
- [TV Announcer] Whiskey Cavalier.
Special sneak preview after the Oscars.
Series premier, February 27th on ABC.
- This is a commercial about buying cars.
- That's a car, this is a
phone, and this is DriveTime.
Do you need a car?
- Yes!
But, I don't have a lot of money.
- Oh great, go online
and check out DriveTime
and save that money!
Their down payments are
$1,000 less on average.
- This is a car commercial.
(inhales deeply)
Will there be a phony focus group?
- Nope!
Just valuable information.
99% of people who apply get approved
even if their credit is, uh!
You can do it in two
minutes, from anywhere.
All you need is your phone.
- I have a phone.
- Everybody does!
- Yeah, I'm done.
I got approved!
- Go to drivetime.com
and get approved in two minutes.
DriveTime. Genius!
- Ready Freddy?
- Let's do it!
- [TV Announcer] It's
Queen, and Adam Lambert.
♪ Do the Fandango ♪
- [TV Announcer] Hosting the Oscars!
♪ Thunderbolt and lightning ♪
♪ Very very frightening ♪
- [TV Announcer] Live!
- Got to make an impression darling!
- [TV Announcer] Only on the Oscars.
Live, Sunday, 8:00 p.m. Eastern,
5:00 p.m. Pacific, on ABC!
(rock music)
- Those are fake!
Never mind, still to
come, music from Juanes.
So you know, our next
guest, as zombie killer
turned zombie on the Walking Dead,
now he is super vigilante Frank Castle
in Marvel's The Punisher,
Season 2 is available now on Netflix,
please say hello to Jon Bernthal!
(audience cheering and applauding)
(rock music)
- How're you doin'?
Everything all right?
- I'm good man.
- Family is good?
- Aah, the family is so good!
- I know you live here in L.A.
Did you bring the whole family to New York
when you were shooting The Punisher?
- No I bring, I guess
I bring my dog family.
I don't bring, the humans stay home.
- I see--
- Yeah, the dogs--
- The humans stay home--
- The babies stay home man,
but the dogs definitely come.
We hightail it across the country.
We can't put 'em on planes so we drive.
- Oh you do?
- We do--
- Is that fun?
- You know, it's a mixed bag.
I drive with my old man--
- Oh, really?
- I do, I do, which is, look.
My old man is the greatest dad on earth.
I love my dad with all my heart.
And what, right on!
(audience applauding)
And you know, for a 70-year old guy
to just pick up and drive cross-country
with three pit-bulls,
that's somethin' man.
But I'll tell you there are
specific rules and regulations
for driving cross-country with my old man.
- Oh he has rules!
- Oh, yeah!
Well first of all you're
not gonna do any driving,
which is great, right?
- He drives the whole time--
- He drives the whole time.
You ain't touchin' the wheel right?
Which is cool, because it's like
havin' a personal driver, right?
But I'm gonna tell you right now.
Jimmy, if you even think
about turning on that radio,
I know it doesn't matter
whether it's music,
it doesn't matter whether it's news,
you will get smacked, with this man hand!
My old man's got those thick, hairy,
just one, you touch that dial, bam!
You know what I mean?
And that's just a day ruiner right there.
- Well why doesn't he--
- He's just, he's got--
- He wants silence in the car?
- He's just very specific.
Look, when you stop for gas,
that is your time to go to the bathroom,
it's time for the dogs
to go to the bathroom,
that's where you're gettin'
your food and your coffee.
If you think about, like a
Starbucks, not gonna happen.
All of a sudden, you're Hollywood man!
Like oh, mister self-serve
Hollywood needs a Starbucks!
(Jimmy laughs) You just get
ripped apart, and it's not like
I'm gettin' a Caramel Macchiato
man, I want a black coffee,
and he's just like, he's not happening--
- Are you allowed to talk
to to him in the car?
- Yes, you are I guess,
and that's the thing.
Like I always think we're gonna have
these deep kind of
father-son bonding moments,
and we start to sometime,
the thing is that
he is constantly screaming at
every one else on the road.
Like he's in a huge rut, and
we say things I definitely
can't say here, but like he's
just driving with hatred!
The entire way across the
country, and it's like--
It just kinda interrupts the moment!
- Yeah sure, yeah!
Does your dad think he's
a good road trip partner?
- I think he would
probably consider himself
the best in the business. (Jimmy laughing)
I think like, and look the truth is look,
he drives fast as hell,
he knows how to go--
- How many days from L.A. to New York?
- He goes straight man,
that man does not stop.
- Really--
- You do not stop that man--
- So you do it in like
two and a half days?
- My man, my man, that's it.
- Wow, wow, maybe you should
get him a job with Uber
or something, you know?
- Oh boy, oh boy--
- It seems like he would
be the ideal driver--
- Yeah, just don't touch the radio.
- So, The Punisher is a rare,
for those who don't follow,
I know all this stuff
and it's all worthless information,
but the rare Marvel character
who doesn't really have
powers necessarily,
do you feel cheated in any way about that?
- Look, I love Frank Castle.
He's a character that has resonated deeply
with the military community
and the law enforcement community,
and it's been an honor to play him.
I wouldn't have it any other way.
- Do you love those days that you get
to beat people up on set?
Is that fun?
- You know man, two things
that I've sworn to myself
that I will never do--
- What are they?
- Come on a show like
this, and talk about, not,
I'm here, but talk about--
- Not that part--
- No, not that part!
- Come on a show like this, that one--
- Come on a show like this and talk
about how I do my own stunts,
or how I get injured doing stunts.
But, I'm gonna do both of those things--
- Okay yeah, go ahead--
- Here's the thing.
I like to do all my own stunts,
I like to do the fighting myself,
I think it's important for the audience
to see Frank Castle in
those moments, and I did,
I broke my hand pretty bad
in the first fight scene
of the season this year--
- Oh, great.
- Yeah, and I knew
exactly when it happened,
it was a three-day fight scene,
and it was the first day,
and I hit somebody and
I knew, I'm a boxer,
I knew immediately it was broken.
But me being the orangutan I am
I didn't say anything to anyone
'cause I didn't wanna get pulled.
I wanted to stay in the fight.
And so the very next thing I had to do
with a broken hand was,
my name Jordan Scott,
a stunt performer, he had to take my hand,
and I had a knife and he had to bash
my broken hand into a table,
and I'm The Punisher man,
it can't just be two
hits, he's gotta like bash
the hell out of my hand on the table.
And so I go to the stunt
coordinator, Eric Linden.
I said, hey man is there anyway
we can switch it to the left hand?
He goes, "What're you doin' man?
"Stay on script, no the
camera's over there,
"like do it, man up!"
All right, ma-bam, ma-bam, ma-bam!
Now I got torn ligaments in my hand right?
So the next thing I
gotta do is I gotta kick
this guy's leg out and he falls down
and I gotta catch him
right in my poor hand,
and I say to him again, hey
man, is there just any chance
we could just move this to the left hand?
And a perfect opportunity to just say,
hey man, my hand's injured--
- Right--
- I didn't say it, and
so I said all right,
this is gonna suck, here we go!
And like my hand, and then
now I've dislocated my hand!
And the very last thing that
we had to do in the scene,
on day three, is these
guys are shooting at me
with automatic weapons and
I throw a bar stool at them.
I don't know, I didn't write it
but that what we got right?
(Jimmy laughs)
And so I go, I gotta--
- Sit on this now!
(audience laughing)
- I go to grab this bar
stool, and I just freeze,
'cause I know with this
mangled mess of a hand
I'm not gonna be able to throw the stool.
Stunt coordinator comes over again,
"Come on man, man up and
throw the damn stool,
"what is the matter with you?"
Oh God, all right, here we go--
- You're not being
treated well on the set--
- No, no, no, he's the best,
I should've said something.
And the thing is, the
directors and the producers,
they're all watching the
scene in Video Village
looking this way, and they don't see
when I grab it with my left hand
I'm supposed to throw that thing at a mat,
but instead I just chucked that thing
and all of a sudden you hear
this (exclaiming loudly)
and it hit that stunt coordinator
right in the leg! (audience laughing)
And that's somethink you
go to the hospital with!
Again!
- He's gotta man up!
Went to the hospital!
(audience applauding)
One non Punisher related
question for you--
- What do you got--
- I read on Monday, and
this is very exciting.
David Chase is going to do a movie,
a prequel to The Sopranos, and I read
that you are going to be in it.
Will you be in this
film? (audience laughing)
You do know what I'm talking about?
You've seen the article?
You're nodding yes, does that mean yes,
I am gonna be in this film?
It does mean yes right there!
(audience cheering and applauding)
Well if you break anything on that set,
please tell David Chase,
or something like that.
- I give you my word.
- I think your father,
made you silent about things
that you shouldn't be.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Well it's great to see you.
Jon Bernthal everybody,
Season 2 of The Punisher,
(audience applauding)
streaming now on Netflix.
Be right back with Juanes!
(rock music)
- [TV Announcer] The Jimmy
Kimmel Live Concert Series
is presented by Mercedes Benz!
The best or nothing.
- [TV Announcer] All this
week, wake up with Oscar!
- Hello Oscar, don't you
look smashing this morning.
- {Male Announcer] Because
the final countdown is one,
and no one does Oscar like GMA!
The stars parties!
The exclusives!
- I think we just found
a new GMA co-anchor.
- [TV Announcer] This week!
- It hasn't always been easy has it?
There have been days,
when you doubted yourself.
(camera clicking)
And days when you were ready to quit.
But you didn't!
Because you had the courage,
to venture into something powerful.
Education!
If I leave you with just
three words of advice,
never
stop
growing.
- [TV Announcer] It's time to go!
Toyota.
Go connected, with a sporty Camry.
With the latest tech.
Compatible with your
favorite apps, and Wi-Fi.
Now, lease a Camry for $219 a month.
Or buy, with $1,500 cash back.
Or go, with a stylish Corolla,
and lease for just $199 a month.
Or buy, with $1,500 cash back
and two years of no-cost
maintenance included.
Go, see your Toyota dealer today.
Toyota!
Let's go places!
(ocean waves)
(gentle soothing music)
- [TV Announcer] Day to night,
and everything in-between.
A vibrant collection of
cultures and activities await!
In greater Fort Lauderdale.
Start planning at sunny.org/letsgo.
- [TV Announcer] The Jimmy
Kimmel Live Concert Series
is presented by Mercedes Benz.
The best, or nothing.
- Now I wanna thank
Regina King, Jon Bernthal,
apologies to Matt Damon, Nightline is next
but first, this song is called LaPlata.
Here is Juanes!
(audience cheering and applauding)
♪ (singing in foreign language) ♪
(lively jazz music)
(comedic trumpet playing)
- Yee-haw!
(orchestral music)
(electronic music)