(rock music)
- [Announcer] A determined bachelor
who needs your help to find love, at six.
- [Announcer] It's Live
with Kelly and Ryan.
Today, from the new film,
Stuber, Kumail Nanjiani.
Plus, television, film and
Broadway star, Bernadette Peters.
Do you know the truth about your dog?
Some adorable adoptable pups will help us
figure out the facts.
All next on Live.
♪ It ain't my fault that
I'm out here gettin loose ♪
And now, here are Kelly
Ripa and Ryan Seacrest.
♪ Blame it on my juice, baby ♪
♪ Ain't my fault that I'm
out here making news ♪
♪ I'm the pudding in the proof ♪
♪ Gotta blame it on my juice ♪
(audience cheers and applauds)
- Hi there, how you doin' today?
♪ Blame it on my juice ♪
♪ Blame it on my juice baby ♪
♪ - Hey. ♪
(audience cheers and chants)
- Happy Birthday, congratulations.
- Thank you all very much.
- Stop.
- [Both] We haven't done anything yet.
- Great minds think.
We've been waiting two weeks to say that.
- Together at the same time.
Monday, July 8, 2019, good morning.
- Hi, good morning.
- You look...
- I'm still jet-lagged.
I've been up
- You look great.
- Since three o'clock this morning.
How about you?
- Oh, well, we're almost done.
- Yeah, I know, I know, I know.
- In just than, less than an hour.
- Very, very jet-lagged.
It's funny, the older you get
the harder it is to
flip over, I feel like.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah, like when I go back
and forth, east to west.
When I do that every week,
when I was younger, it was easier.
Now, it's painful.
- Painful.
- But you were on a
European jet lag, right?
- Yes, yes, I'm on European jet lag.
- So it's dinner time.
- I'm starving.
I wanna eat pasta right now.
- Oh my gosh, how was it?
- It was great.
Let me, can I show you, can
I bore you with some photos?
You know how I love to show you my--
(audience cheers)
Yeah, you're welcome.
Let me just say that we
went home to the house
where my husband grew up
as a small child, okay?
So we went to the house.
This was not his birthplace house.
This is where they moved
when he was a small kid.
I don't know how old he is in this photo.
I'm gonna say like four or five years old.
This is where they moved.
This tiny little beach
town in southern Italy.
This one over here is my
adorable husband, right there.
That's his brother, Mike
and that's my sister-in-law, Adriana.
There's my mother-in-law right there.
Sorry about my fingernails.
They look ridiculous, but these
were vacation fingernails.
And that's my grandfather-in-law,
who has passed away,
may he rest in peace.
- What a beautiful picture.
- So we recreated it with our group,
so there we are in front of the house.
They were on the inside of the fence here.
We're on the outside of the fence.
(audience and Ryan laugh)
- We rang the bell and nobody was home.
Nobody was home but there we are.
It was just very emotional to go back
and to have these photos
and to picture my--
- What was Mark's
reaction when he got back?
- He was very emotional.
He goes, "It's exactly the same,
"except the trees have gotten bigger."
It's exactly as he remembered it.
We pulled up in a minivan,
as we (video blips)
and we...
everything is like a tiny little car,
so we looked like we were in a truck.
And when we pulled into
the street, he goes,
"Everybody's going to
come out of the front door
"or hang over the terraces."
And like clockwork, it was like..
- Oh, look at the tourists.
- Hmm, hmm.
And it was just, we
started playing a game,
count the nonnas on the terrace.
I'm like, how many nonnas do you think
we're gonna see on the terrace?
The kids were like, "We'll see
12 nonnas on the terraces."
So anyway, I took some
pictures of my husband
because I love to
photograph him on vacation--
- He's shirtless.
(audience laughs)
- He is shirtless, yes.
There he is here.
Yep, mmm hmmm.
(audience catcalls)
You're welcome America and
Canada, you're welcome, yes.
- It's depressing.
- Plus, my kids, he's
by the way, I just want to
point out in this photo,
he's surrounded by my children,
who will no longer let
me post photos of them,
so there he is.
Here we are, we got a little lost,
he refused to ask for directions,
but he thought he could
just find it himself.
- It looks like an ad, doesn't it?
It looks like an ad for sun
- Isn't that great?
- It's like a Ray-Ban ad.
- Yeah, it's great.
- I had no idea my picture's being taken.
- Here he is with his, there we are.
- See?
- Yep.
- There he is with my
doppleganger son of his,
like the two twins.
- They look like boys.
- There they are the boys.
- Yeah.
Here they are at a wall of bougainvillea.
Finally, I said to him,
"Hey, will you do me a favor,
"because I'm gonna show some
of these pictures on the air,
"will you take a picture of me,
"because I just want to be able
"to prove that I was on this trip."
And so he did, he took a picture of me.
I don't know if you can see it.
(audience laughs)
That's me.
If you look past the flowers,
that's me floating on a pool float.
It's like a giant pillow.
They called it a ravioli.
I'm not kidding, they call
it the floating ravioli.
But that's the one picture he took of me.
There it is.
Then I just wanted to show you snakes.
There were also snakes on this trip.
They were free.
You didn't even have to
pay extra for the snakes.
- You sent me a text,
you said one word, snakes
and I said oh okay.
- He was like, what
does that mean, snakes?
There are snakes.
- What does that mean,
- everywhere?
- I don't know why they keep finding me.
People were like, no,
there are no snakes here.
I go, I am photographing snakes.
- There's actually a
second photo of you here.
If you take a closer look,
I think that's you in the
shadow there, isn't it?
(audience laughs)
- Oh yeah that's me.
- That's me.
- Thank you.
- Good shot.
- Thanks though.
- [Man] Very muscular.
- Yeah, you look very
fit in that silhouette.
- My shadows are very muscular.
- Your shadows look great.
- My shadows have a lot of curves.
- Mark didn't capture you,
but he captured your shadow.
- He did that, I captured my own shadow.
Mark took a picture of plants.
- Plants with someone
on a floating ravioli.
- I accidentally drifted
by on a pool float.
How was your vacation?
- It was great.
- 'Cause you were gone a long time.
- I was gone a long time as well.
I had to go overseas
for a little convention
for the radio show, which was in Cannes.
Then I went back to L.A. for a day.
Then I went to Greece to
get some sun afterwards.
- Greece is the word.
- It's just beautiful,
the people are great,
the food is great, but during
all of this, something,
you know, because I've got this niece now,
every first is a big deal in the family
so my sister, she was so
nervous about traveling
with baby Flora for the
first time on the plane.
So here they are.
I just wanna show you, this is
Jimmy and Meredith and Flora
(audience coos)
on their first flight.
- Adorable.
- And she was so concerned
about how Flora was gonna do,
was she gonna manage,
was she gonna be a mess,
was she gonna be screaming and crying.
Well looks like she enjoyed herself.
(audience laughs)
- I can't believe she is my size.
- She's our size.
- She is our size.
That is the outfit I wore
on the show last week.
- I was gonna say. (laughs)
One of the things I discovered,
because you know, I love to eat and snack,
especially when I'm on vacation.
I took the clocks out of my room
so I didn't know what time it
was in the middle of the night
or what time it was in the morning,
so I slept 'til I woke up.
It's the greatest thing ever.
- You slept until I texted you.
- Snakes.
- Pictures of snakes.
- Leave me alone.
But you know, you and Mark have
PB and Js all the time.
I had every day, every
day on vacation, a PBJB.
Have you had that?
- What's a PBJB?
- Peanut butter, jelly and bacon.
(audience exclaims)
You're welcome as well,
America and Canada.
I leave you with this treat today.
Make yourself a PBJB,
peanut butter jelly ba.
You're shaking, are you cited?
- I'm so cited about that.
- This is what you guys
should be making every night.
'Cause Mark loves to
eat these in bed, right?
- Oh my God, it's his favorite thing.
But you know what's so funny is?
We were in Corsica first
and then we went to Italy
and we did not have access.
I mean, I'm sure we could have conjured up
access to peanut butter and jelly,
but we like to eat local.
We like to eat what local people eat,
so we were having lots of
- Olive butter.
- Fresh food.
Fresh fish and fresh,
we had pasta every day
and it was homemade and we went to a farm
where they make the burrata
and it was incredible.
We did the whole thing.
And he, of course, because he was
without peanut butter
and jelly for two weeks,
lost five pounds.
(audience laughs)
- 'Cause he needed to.
- He lost five pounds.
- Yeah, you saw him in that shot.
- Just skipping peanut butter and jelly.
It's so irritating.
(audience laughs)
- We'll start sneaking in,
no kidding, I know.
I mean, start sneaking the bacon in there.
He'll regain it.
- Just slide it right in.
He'll never notice.
- See if he notices.
- He'll never notice.
Lots of news over the last couple days.
These two earthquakes in
southern California, big deal.
Real serious.
There was two back-to-back, basically
and the last one, 7.1, which
is eight times stronger
than the first one.
- Eleven times.
- Eleven times, stronger
than the first one, right?
- That's so interesting, 'cause
I was watching that on CNN.
They were explaining it.
- The decimal, right?
- So you go, okay, so first one was 6.4,
- The Richter.
- And then the 7.1, you
go, oh, it's not that much.
It doesn't seem like
that much big of a shift
and apparently--
- It's exponential.
It's that times.
- Yeah, every decimal is
that full amount times.
- Times whatever.
- So it is significant.
Have you been?
I've been in them before.
I was not there for the Northridge one,
I had not moved to L.A. yet.
- Oh, you're kidding.
- But I have been there for smaller ones,
threes and fours and even those scare ya.
- My son was out in
California, my oldest son,
and he was in L.A. proper,
but he said they could
feel the earthquakes.
They felt them.
- You kinda, after you feel
one, you stop sleeping naked
because
(audience laughs)
you just never know when you're gonna
have to run into the door jamb, right?
- [Man] Shoes by the side of the bed.
- Shoes by the side of the bed.
But here, it's safe to sleep naked.
(audience laughs)
- Well, it depends on
whose house you're in.
- Well generally, I
like to sleep in my own.
- I mean, don't sleep naked in my house,
'cause the kids will
walk in at any second.
They'll be, "Don't you
ever put clothes on?"
And I'm like, "Don't you knock?"
(audience laughs)
Anyway, it's so interesting.
There's so much to talk about in sports.
I mean, the Women's Soccer
(audience cheers)
- Incredible, so great.
- I, who don't watch, watched and I said,
I cannot believe I've been missing
this sport for so many years.
- It's incredible, right?
- Yeah.
You know, my husband and
my kids always watch soccer
and I just drifted in and out.
God, they are so, so good.
- So good.
- I was so just
unabashedly happy for them.
- Well, they're gonna be celebrated.
I think Wednesday there's a
big parade here in the city.
- Yes, that would be downtown.
(audience cheers)
- Downtown, yeah.
Then, Alex, Alex Morgan, she's nominated
for Best Female Athlete at the ESPYs,
which also airs on Wednesday, right?
- [Man] Yeah.
- Incredible.
- On ABC, yeah.
- Fabulous.
- So congratulations to that team.
(audience cheers)
If you haven't been watching,
you've been missing.
Did you watch any of the tennis?
Did you see Coco?
- I know, so I don't follow tennis,
but Mark keeps saying, oh my
God, you've gotta follow tennis
because there's this young
girl named Coco, is it Gauff?
Who is 15 years old and is really
on this winning streak at Wimbledon.
So I have a 16-year-old
son and my daughter,
who just turned 18, and--
- You just picturing
it, thinking about it.
- You picture them at 15.
Any 15-year-olds here, 15?
Hi, hi there.
So 15, give me the rundown.
What are you into?
- [Girl] Backstreet Boys.
- Backstreet Boys?
- You're into the Backstreet boys.
- It's so funny, we were too as teenagers.
- Somebody down here was
yelling, what are you into?
- [Girl] Dance.
- You're into dance?
- Dance?
- Are you a competitive dancer?
- No.
- Don't clam up now.
(audience laughs)
This is your big moment.
- [Girl] We love to dance.
We also love musical theater
and acting and singing.
- [Ryan] Musical theater,
acting and singing.
- Okay, all right.
So, I want you to picture that you're--
- You're at the Oscars.
- You're at the Oscars
and you're on stage.
- And you've just accepted.
- And this is for all the marbles.
You're about to win the
Academy Award and you're 15.
How do you feel?
Are you freaking out?
- [Girls] Yes.
- This girl has no freak-out, apparently.
She does not freak out.
- She's so poised.
- It's amazing to see, as you were saying,
a 15-year-old with that kind of poise
and the talent and the skill,
but I too, I mean, I don't have kids,
but I too was thinking
about just like how--
- I can't get them to hang
up their towel on a hook.
- Yeah, how disciplined, how disciplined
one must be as a young child.
- Hang up your towel on a hook
so it doesn't get mildewed.
You can use a towel more than once.
(Ryan laughs)
Right?
(audience cheers and applauds)
- Just 'cause my mom used to say that,
I now leave them on the
floor, just to spite.
- You just deliberately
leave them on the floor.
- Yeah, then I have to pick them up.
- Atta boy.
- I can't remember in years past,
I was watching some of the Wimbledon
and they split screen action.
They're very, they assume--
- [Man] They do have more of that
that we have a lot of capacity as viewers,
'cause they're watching two
matches at the same time.
- What do you mean?
You mean they play two matches?
I thought they split screen so you don't
have to do this the whole time.
- No, they split screen two action shots.
They did, I was like.
They're very ambitious
and they think that I have
a lot of capacity to
understand what's going on
but you can watch two matches at once.
I had not seen that before.
I've seen the split
where they're volleying
but this was a split of live
action, two different courts.
Really challenging.
(audience laughs)
I was exhausted--
- Right.
- after watching.
- It sounds exhausting.
And the whole scoring system
is always challenging for me.
Because it goes in, what is it, 15.
It goes by 15.
- [Man] Oh yeah, 15, 30.
- Until you get to 40.
- Yeah, and I'm like, I
don't know what comes next.
- Add in, add out, your love,
my love, our love, we love.
Today, we love the show.
Today on the show, Kumail
Nanjiani is with us.
(audience applauds)
He's got a great new movie.
It's very funny, Stuber.
We'll see him again.
- And Bernadette Peters is back.
She's brought some pups
who are up for adoption.
(audience applauds)
- There is a lab mix.
- Are you looking?
- I'm not looking, but there's a lab mix
and I'm a sucker for a lab.
And we're gonna see if we
know the facts about our dogs
when we play a game of Truth or Tail.
(audience applauds)
- Get it?
- I got it.
- But now it's time for Stump
the Hosts travel trivia.
Let's do it.
(audience applauds and cheers)
- [Audience] Stump the Hosts.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ (foreign language) ♪
♪ Don't stop the party ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- Oh yeah.
Christine Mills from
Bohemia, is that right?
Bohemia, Long Island.
- Yay, woo hoo.
(audience cheers)
- [Ryan] Long Island.
- Bohemia, that sounds
like where I wanna live.
- [Christine] It's very exotic.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you're very bohemian.
- All right, today,
both our studio audience
and you watching at home can weigh in
on which statement you think is true.
Go to KELLYANDRYANNOW.COM to vote
and just for voting,
you could have a chance
to win your own Kelly & Ryan mug.
- Oh, look at it.
- There she is.
- Look at her.
(speaker muffled by audience)
- Just look at it's majesty.
- So we've got Mitzi Hovre
from Dripping Springs, Texas
on the phone, who watches us on KVUE.
Good morning, Mitzi, how are you?
- [Mitzi] Hi, I'm good. How are y'all?
- We're great.
- We're good, thanks.
- What are you up to this morning?
- [Mitzi] Good.
Oh, I was just fixing
to go running with my daughter
and y'all called, so I
get to take the day off.
- Were you gonna go running?
- [Mitzi] Yeah, I was gonna go running,
but now I don't have to.
(audience laughs)
= No, you can still run.
This won't take long.
- I just want you to know,
this phone call is gonna
take about two minutes.
- You shouldn't blow
off your run for this.
As a matter of fact, we'll speed it up
right now so you can get to it.
- [Mitzi] Okay.
- We've got
- two statements from Mitzi.
We're trying to guess which one is true.
If you stump us, you win the mug, okay?
- [Mitzi] Okay.
- First of her statements,
when I was younger,
I could stick my entire fist in my mouth.
- Oh, I know somebody that can do that.
- [Mitzi] You do?
- Yeah, I do, I do.
- You can call me by my name.
- [Mitzi] Oh yeah.
- Can you do that too?
I've never tried it.
If anything, now is not the time.
Or, I made it to the semi-finals
of the Dallas Cowboys Cheerleader tryouts.
- Oh my gosh, I so wanna believe that.
- [Mitzi] Oh. (laughs)
- Okay, so I'm looking at you.
I'm trying to figure out,
I wish your hand was in this photo
So I could see your mouth to fist ratio.
(audience and Ryan laugh)
- So she could scale it.
- [Mitzi] Really we can, yeah.
- Okay, so what was the key to
making it to the semi-finals
in the Dallas Cowboy Cheerleader tryouts?
- [Mitzi] Well, you had
to have your own vignette
and you had to do it for 90 seconds
and my aunt was a, she was a dancer,
so she taught me a dance ahead of time
and then you had to go and perform
and you did it as a
group and everybody just,
they played music and you
just kind of dance around.
I knew what I was gonna do, so I did that.
- Hmmm.
- Suspect.
- Okay.
- [Man] Discover her.
- Yeah, how did you discover your talent?
- Yeah, how'd you discover your fist--
(gong sounds)
- Oh shoot.
- Talent.
- How'd you discover your fist talent?
- [Mitzi] You know, I don't know.
I just used to do that and
a boy in my junior high,
he did it too and so we got put,
our pictures got put in the yearbook
puttin' our fists in our mouths.
Then I had to quit in high school.
I guess my fists got a little bit big,
'cause I started ripping
the sides of my mouth.
- [Man] Ow.
(audience moans)
- That sounds dangerous.
- This is taking a dark turn.
- Let's see, what does the audience think?
What do you guys think?
Wow.
See, okay, so okay.
I used to watch that show, you know,
about the Dallas Cowboy
Cheerleader tryouts,
they had a show on, y'all--
- Y'all remember?
- Y'all wanna say y'all,
y'all remember that show?
- Y'all remember that?
- And I remember them having
a very choreographed routine
that they had to memorize
in like one second.
I don't remember that
being able to freestyle.
- I agree, and I thought--
- [Mitzi] You know, the freestyle
is the very beginning one.
That's the pre-round,
and then the semi-finals
is when they teach you a dance
- Now we're in trouble.
- [Mitzi] and then you do a kick routine
- [Man] All right, lock it in guys.
Lock it in.
- and you're
- [Mitzi] Performing
in front of the judges.
- But that's not what you said
when I questioned you under
intensive questioning, Mitzi.
- [Man] Lock it in.
- Remember, I said.
- I was right here.
- Right, you were here for it.
- I was here, I was right here.
- We were all right here, the witnesses.
- All right, what are we going with?
- I don't know.
- Originally I thought--
- I wanna say fist in mouth.
- That's what I thought too.
- And because I'm looking at her great,
beautiful, wide smile,
(Mitzi laughs)
- Which also could work
to the cheerleading thing,
but I think it's fist in mouth, guys.
- We're going against the audience.
- What do you thinK?
- Is it fist in mouth?
- [Mitzi] That's true.
(everyone cheers)
- Got it.
Go with the gut always, right?
You haven't lost it, you got it.
- I still got it.
- Well, even though
you didn't win the mug,
we're gonna spin the wheel
and see what you're playing for here.
(wheel clicks)
Still got it.
(audience cheers)
- Be nice though if you
could do that, yeah.
- All right, what do we have?
- Ooh, this is a great prize.
The JW Marriott Cancun
Resort and Spa in Mexico.
Seven days, six nights in
a premium ocean-view room.
It includes $1400 food
and beverage credit,
a spa treatment per person.
It's a prize valued at $7500.
You have 20 seconds and
only one guess, Mitzi.
Good luck.
- [Mitzi] Okay, thanks.
- Okay, Mitzi, on Friday's show,
we talked with Ricky Gervais.
In what town outside London
did Ricky say he lives?
- [Mitzi] Okay, what town?
Oh, it was Hampstead.
- You got it.
- Yes.
(audience cheers)
- [Announcer] Congratulations,
you and a guest will enjoy
seven days and six nights
lounging in on-coast luxury
at JW Marriott Cancun Resort and Spa,
boasting an extensive selection
of upscale combinations.
Guests will enjoy endless
beaches through turquoise waters,
expansive pools, a variety
of on-site restaurants,
creating fresh and authentic
tastes, a Mayan-inspired spa
and much more.
Your prize is valued
at approximately $7500.
(audience cheers)
- That looks great.
- Woo.
- [Mitzi] Whoa, thank
y'all, thank you so much.
- Congratulations.
- [Mitzi] I have kind of a sad story.
We came to New York, we planned our trip
around y'all last year and then, you know,
'cause you can't get
tickets until a few months
ahead of time, they don't put it on there,
and then, we were there
right when y'all were gone.
We were gonna come.
- Ohhh.
- You mean for vacation.
- [Man] Yeah, but now you have a better--
- But listen.
- But now
- you're gonna take vacation.
- You're gonna take a trip and
tickets are not hard to get.
(audience cheers)
They're free.
- Right, we'll put you on the list.
- [Mitzi] Thanks y'all.
- Oh, they're not easy.
- We'll put you, you know what,
but she's on the phone with us.
We can put her on hold
and give her tickets
for when she comes back.
- [Man] Yeah, if she's here,
we'll give her tickets.
- Yeah, we'll put--
- We're gonna work this out
and get you on your run, okay?
- [Mitzi] Oh, thank you.
(audience laughs)
- All right Mitzi, listen.
One more thing.
You have to help us make the day
of a lucky member of our studio audience
who's gonna receive a
$500 gift certificate
from Barnes & Noble,
so please pick a number
(audience cheers)
between one and 212.
- [Mitzi] Okay, number 28.
- Which one?
- [Mitzi] 28.
- [Both] 28.
- Right there.
(audience yells and cheers)
- Congratulations.
Mitzi, have a good job.
Thanks for watching, enjoy your trip.
We'll be right back with Kumail Nanjiani.
♪ ...here gettin' loose ♪
♪ Gotta blame it on the goose ♪
- [Announcer] Still ahead on Live,
we'll test our dog knowledge
with Bernadette Peters
and some adoptable pups.
We'll go to the inbox,
here comes the questions.
Coming up next, Kumail Nanjiani.
- [Announcer] Most days,
this is just a grip
like this is just a curve
and this a toy.
But here, it becomes something more.
It's the instant she knows she's got this.
It's when he finally beats dad.
And when his day--
(beep)
- [Kelly] Wrestling
superstar Dave Bautista,
please welcome Kumail Nanjiani.
♪ Hey there, you're an allstar ♪
♪ Get your game on, go play ♪
♪ Hey now, you're a rock star ♪
♪ Get the show on, get paid ♪
- Woo
(audience cheers)
- Hi, hi, good to see you.
- Good to see you.
- Good to see you again.
Welcome back.
- Thank you.
Guys, why is it so smoky in here?
What is going on?
- Thank you for noticing.
Apparently, they are special
effects for our trivia game.
- You can injure a lot of people
with this fist in mouth chat.
(audience and Ryan laugh)
- Do you know it?
- Can I do that?
- Yeah, I'm asking.
- No.
- I'm not gonna try it, nice try.
No.
- Now you, as I shook your
hand, I notice that you've got--
(beep)
...don't believe that
it's a flying saucer.
I believe that it's an
unidentified flying object,
which could be--
- Well, you think like
a saucer and a teacup.
- Yeah, no.
- It's not that.
- No, I don't believe that they--
- We are arguing about the shape of it?
- I believe that there, I don't even,
and the military says that they don't know
but I think they have to know, right?
- I like that you're
air-quoting everything.
They don't know
but they have to know.
- But they have to know.
- But they, yeah, whisper.
Whisper, they won't hear us.
Did you recently throw the first
pitch at the baseball game?
- I threw the first pitch, yeah.
(audience laughs)
- [Ryan] Did it go over the plate?
- [Kelly] Okay, wait, wait, wait.
- [Kumail] It went over the plate.
- Okay, can we show that
picture one more time?
That looks like a staged photo,
like they almost superimposed
your head onto an action shot.
- Yeah, I'm in front of a green screen.
I threw out the first pitch.
- That's a great shot.
- That photographer was amazing.
Every picture from there, I look
like Robert Redford or something.
- It's terrifying, isn't it?
I've done a night.
- How did it go for you?
- It didn't go over the plate.
- Mmmm.
- What about you?
- It went over the plate.
Well, it didn't--
- Good for you.
- Thank you Daddy.
(Kumail laughs)
Thank you Daddy.
- Daddy, we're gonna talk to Daddy.
More with Kumail about
what it's like to attend
his first WWE wrestling
match, right after the plug.
Stay with us.
(audience cheers)
- [Announcer] Still ahead
on Live, Bernadette Peters.
- From WGLA 24-7 News, this
is Good Morning Washington.
On your side.
We begin with a breaking news alert.
- And we are following
breaking news right now.
Just an immense amount of rain
hitting the DMV right now.
Let's get right out to John
Gonzalez, who's in Arlington,
and last time we checked in with him,
just some incredible images.
That red car behind you, John, submerged
and it looks like personal belongings
coming out of the doors
and into the water.
Good morning.
- Just a good morning
and a scary situation.
Many scary situations this morning
throughout the entire D.C. area.
You know, we started off
reporting this morning
in Boyds, Maryland, doing something
completely unrelated on
the Women's World Cup
and the storm came through there first
and it continued down the I-270 corridor
and now it is coming through
Arlington and the D.C. city
with this unbelievable amount of rain
and take a look.
This is Kennebec Street
and 11th here in Arlington
and you can see that car, that Hundai,
is almost completely submerged.
There was a call.
We were hearing the scanners,
the emergency scanners,
and there was a call reported for a woman
on top of a stranded vehicle.
We believe that's the case here,
so the woman is no longer in the vehicle,
no longer on the roof of the vehicle,
so we are hoping that she's
been able to get some help.
That's the hope, and now
that car is just submerged,
but you can see just all
of the standing water here
and this happened in a matter of minutes.
I mean, we're talking torrential
rain, just too much rain
in a short period of
time overwhelmed the area
and you can see that car is now reversing.
You hear it all the time, I know
it sounds cliche, folks,
turn around, don't drown.
Well here's a perfect
situation, a perfect example
of what we talk about when
we say that on the air.
Here's a small vehicle,
another sedan similar
to the one that's stuck
just to the right of us,
trying to get through
that standing water here
right next to Westover Park and they are
having to now reverse, a very good idea,
but they're gonna have
to do that carefully
because you've got just as much
standing water now behind them.
Back to this vehicle here, red Hundai,
you see the bag on top
of the roof, Steve Rudin.
We're hoping for the best.
We're hoping that the news is good,
that this woman was able to
get out without any injuries.
We don't see any paramedics
or first responders
right here directly where this vehicle is.
They are up the hill a bit,
but just a scary situation, Steve.
Just too much rain.
The manhole is just
completely overwhelmed.
The sewer system just
can't take this much rain.
- All right John.
If we could just stay on this
picture here for a moment,
and this is exactly
what flash flooding is.
If you look at the topography,
you'll notice that it's sort
of in a low-lying area here
and when we looked over
toward the right earlier,
you could see there was a bit of a hill,
so all this water is cascading downward
and it's all pooling in this one location
and this is exactly what
flash flooding is all about.
It doesn't take very long,
it happens in a flash
and it could happen in a minute,
it could happen in two minutes
and this is why you don't
go across the roads.
You just don't know how deep the water is.
You might say to yourself or think,
hey I've traveled this
route over and over again.
There's no problems at all.
It looks like it's two or three inches.
Before you know it, it's
six inches, it's ten inches,
it's two feet of water, and
once you get that much water,
your car is going to be shot and it's
not gonna be working and
it's not a good thing.
Johnny G, we'll let
him talk to that person
but this is what it looks
like right now over toward
Tenleytown and upper northwest
D.C., National Harbor.
Heavy rain continues to fall.
This has now been going
on for what 20, 25 minutes
with those torrential downpours.
395 heading into the city, at
least traffic is getting in
but I do think that because
of the timing of this storm,
the heavy rainmaker, that
a lot of folks have put off
leaving to go to work and a lot of people,
thank goodness, are still on vacation
because they're enjoying
the long holiday weekend.
The Whitehurst looking good,
at least in terms of movement.
Both directions headed
over toward Georgetown
and this right here is
over toward K Street
and the Kennedy Center.
Flash flood warning does continue.
All areas inside and close
to the Capital Beltway,
whether you are in
Silver Spring or Wheaton
or if you are in Anacostia, Oxen Hill,
National Harbor, Capitol
Hill, you get the point.
Lots of wet weather on the way.
All this slowly drifts
on off toward the south.
Alexandria about another
half hour to 45 minutes
and then you are going
to start to dry out.
Along with the heavy rain,
you may hear a few rumbles of thunder,
so if you're going to be driving about,
definitely use extreme caution.
Let's over to Veronica.
- A good portion of our area
under a flash flood emergency
right now and this could last
as late as two to 3 p.m. today
with the storms that
have been moving through
with the pockets of moderate
and some very heavy rain.
Flooding really is the main issue
over the next couple of hours.
I wanna go back to this
graphic, 'cause it really shows
the amount of rain that we
have received in some portions
of our area, not over a 12-hour period
but over in just an hour
to an hour and a half.
You're looking at some
of the roadways there,
Bradley River there, where the
water has at times been high.
We've seen that high
water in many locations
throughout Montgomery County, upwards
two three, four, close
to five inches of rain.
There's a look at McLean,
close to five inches of rain,
which is why we've seen those
water rescues occurring.
If it hasn't been high water
covering the roads near you,
it's been about the low visibility,
not just from the rainfall
rates, which have been high,
about one to two inches per hour,
but also the fog, that fog
deck really thickening up now.
Okay, so here's the latest on radar.
This is the area that we've been tracking
over the last two, three hours
and you can see it right
here, now moving just
south and east of the district,
that southeast side of
the beltway right now,
through Prince George's County,
through Anne Arundel County
but also now Charles County
seeing some of that heavy rain
and eventually, this is
going to be passing off
to the northeast, so we may
see improving conditions,
but keep in mind the
roads in many instances
have been covered with water,
ponding with a lot of road spray,
but also the rivers and streams.
They're gonna continue to rise.
What's an interesting feature right here
with this weather
boundary across the area,
you see this right here,
you've got this heavy rain
coming south and east and then this area
throughout Prince George's County,
throughout Calvert and
Saint Mary's, coming north.
That's convergent.
That's right along the
front and that means
that all that moisture in the atmosphere
is pooling right along this
weather boundary near us.
So for Fairfax, for
the district right now,
just south of Bowie down 301,
down to 95 and areas east
of Manassas, that's where the
heaviest rain is right now.
These are the rainfall rates
at upwards two inches per hour.
Look at the visibility
out there right now.
This is just one of the
cameras, as we have one out just
a little bit showing you
the Capitol in the distance
where the visibilities have
dropped under a half mile.
Alexandria, you're seeing
that heavy rain right now.
Mount Vernon and areas toward Clinton,
soon heading into Brandywine,
soon heading into Indian Head
and soon also Waldorf, right down 301.
So if you live in this area
here throughout Charles County
throughout Saint Mary's
and Calvert County,
I'd say, don't get on the road right now.
If you can, wait about another
hour and a half to two hours.
Maybe you've got a doctor's
appointment somewhere.
Maybe your kids have summer camp.
I tell you what folks, they're better off
inside and so are you.
You're seeing these dark, shaded counties.
That's western Howard County
under a flash flood warning.
That is until 11:45 p.m.
Look at Montgomery County,
Gaithersburg, Germantown,
Damascus area over toward Potomac Falls,
as well as Laurel.
This also, your county
under a flash flood warning.
That continues too up until
11:15, so many of these going
as late as noon and as
mentioned, right down south
throughout Charles County and
areas soon to be Saint Mary's
and Calvert County that are
gonna go a little longer.
Hard to see there.
I wanna go back to that shot
because really the bridge,
the Woodrow Wilson Bridge,
obscured in the distance.
This is our National Harbor camera
and you can see even the
top of the wheel there
really obscured by the low
cloud deck, the visibility
and the rain that has just
been pouring across the area.
Here's a look at the Capitol
and another look at the radar.
Right now in the District, you
folks, if you're in Westin,
if you're in Adelphi, if you're in Bowie,
you may see some improvement
right now with that rain
that has just been pouring,
but for again, any of you,
if you live near some
creeks, streams, rivers,
know that the water still
could be rising quite high.
All this kind of flowing
from north to south.
Heavy rain continues across the area.
There's our I-270 camera
around Clarksburg Road,
but sitting not too far from me
is Adriana Hopkins and
Mel, who's been with us
all morning long as well, keeping an eye
on what's been happening on social media
with this heavy rain that
of course we told you about
early this morning on
Good Morning Washington.
- Absolutely, Veronica
and this is where we really
want to encourage everyone
to follow our team on social media
because we do have people
all over the place.
As they were driving into work,
they got caught in this rain and storm
We have people, our crews,
that we've sent out to
look for these areas
where the roads are
flooded and where there
might be some water rescues
happening right now.
So really,
- We were actually on the air earlier
and nothing was happening.
We were talking about we're expecting rain
and then all of the sudden,
sometime in the eight o'clock hour,
the rain started falling very
heavily and as Sam Sweeney,
our live reporter, showed us,
he was out in Potomac
and Montgomery County,
and the flash flooding
just came up so suddenly
on some of these back roads.
They're totally washed out.
- [Adriana] Absolutely, and
looking here at the pictures
in the video that we have
from earlier this morning,
this is the GW Parkway that
you're looking at right here
and you can see just how much
water there is on the roads
and how this, as you said,
Melanie, happened immediately.
We knew that this was happening.
We knew it was coming, but
it all of a sudden just came
in torrential waves of water.
This is in North Potomac right here.
When I say follow our
team on social media,
if you follow John Gonzalez right now,
you can see that he is tweeting
his view from Arlington right now.
He says, "There's a lot of lightening.
"There is torrential rain."
He said that manholes
there are overwhelmed
and they've experienced a
number of road closures.
There are people tweeting on
social media about our Metro.
Virginia Square Metro Station
has a major water leak right now.
Here's a video right now of Arlington.
You can see the visibility
there is extremely poor.
The FAA has tweeted out this morning
that there are several
major airports affected
by this weather, from
Miami and Fort Lauderdale
all the way up north to LaGuardia
and those airports that
could experience delays,
they do include Reagan and Dulles as well.
Montgomery County dealing with
a lot of creeks and streams
that are overflowing with water.
This right here is right
outside of our studios
here in Ross and you can see
people trying to make their way
with these umbrellas, but
again, this rain is heavy
and it is swift, and just
people trying to run through it
and get to some dry space.
- It doesn't seem like with this system,
Veronica hasn't mentioned
anything about thunderstorms
or lightening or any high winds.
It simply has been a
lot of water coming down
and causing flooding problems.
Our John Gonzalez is out
live for us right now.
John, where are you and it looks like
we've got a water rescue
behind you going on.
- Yeah, well here's the situation.
The first responders were here, Melanie,
the Arlington County Fire Department,
but they've moved on.
They've got so many calls,
they made sure that everyone
here in this neighborhood
is safe and they've moved on
but you can see what was left behind.
You have neighbors helping
the driver of this vehicle,
trying to get her belongings
out of the vehicle.
A couple of minutes ago, a
couple of guys were gonna try
to push the car back.
Not so sure that's a good idea,
but this is the young
lady here, the driver,
with the pink jacket.
She tells me that the
car was actually parked
and she came out to try to move
it because she saw the rain
coming in strong and the
waters starting to pick up
and she couldn't move it in time.
So, that's the situation here
on Kennebec Street and 11th.
You have a tremendous
amount of standing water.
Just flash flooding at it's best here
and take a look at here.
This is next to the apartment building.
You have the kiddos looking
out, witnessing something
pretty dramatic and you
can see the walkway here.
The stairwell is completely
flooded that leads
to their apartments and just so much rain.
That's what we've been
talking about this morning.
Just so much rain in
a short period of time
and a tremendous amount of flooding
and you've also got lightening.
This is right next to the Westover Park,
just to give you a lay of the land.
In fact, John, if you pan
over to the ball field,
you can see the outfield
of the baseball field
completely under water and
you have now several cars
that were parked here on Kennebec
that are now under water.
Some of the water is receding.
This vehicle not as submerged as it was
when we first arrived
about 20 minutes ago.
That's the good news with
some of these storms.
You get the water comes
in, the flash flooding,
and then the waters recede pretty quickly,
but it's very, very dangerous.
We saw a man trying to
go down the road here.
He quickly realized not a
good idea and he reversed.
We were able to talk to him on camera.
He says he had an
appointment he had to get to
but he realized it was
just way too dangerous,
not worth it, and you can
see some of these vehicles
are literally turning around as they see
the standing water here at
11th and Kennebec in Arlington.
All of this started in
the Boyds, Maryland area,
Frederick County, and it
moved down the I-270 corridor.
We were actually live up there,
doing a story on the women
winning the World Cup,
and the storm was almost following us
as we came back down into Arlington
and here you have it now, coming
through Arlington and D.C.
Just a tremendous amount of rain.
A very scary situation here
but the good news is the driver is okay.
- Johnny, you mentioned that
you've been caught in the rain
ever since this morning when
you were in Boyds, Maryland
and suddenly the rain just poured down
on you during one of our live shots.
Explain what you have seen
so far from that moment,
then you moved down to Arlington
and then where you are now,
how did you see that
weather progress and change?
- You know, we had a live report coming up
at around seven o'clock this morning
and we saw those clouds moving in
and I told my photographer, John,
something's about to drop
here, we better take some cover
and within minutes, the rain
just came down, lightening.
It's interesting to watch,
almost like watching a radar,
as we were driving down
270 onto the beltway,
we can see the storm behind
us, literally following us,
and now we are here in
Arlington and it caught up to us
and this is what it's creating.
This is the same kind of
situation we were witnessing
up north in upper Montgomery
County, Gaithersburg,
Germantown, a number of road closures
because of this very
thing, flash flooding,
and now it has hit D.C. and Arlington
and this is the situation.
You've got, not necessarily cars that were
on the road driving, but
cars that were parked
and are now in the middle of the road.
That's how powerful this water can be.
When you have a tremendous
amount of water,
the power is just enormous.
You have now a gentleman who's pulled up
in a pickup truck here.
It looks like he's getting
ready to help this young lady
try to get this car out of here.
But just a dramatic scene.
When we first got here, we were concerned
that there were people
inside, maybe children,
because you have little stuffed animals
that came out of the
car, personal belongings
that literally floated away.
But the good news again, we've been able
to talk to the driver, she
didn't want to talk on camera,
but just a startling morning for her.
She says, again, she
saw the standing water.
She saw the road quickly
submerged and she tried
to move her car and it was just too late.
She did not have enough time.
- All right, John, you
know, we were watching
the situation unfold
behind you with that car
and it's really a little
difficult for us to assess
just how heavily the rain is coming down
looking at the TV screen.
What would you say right now?
Is it a moderate rainfall?
Is is tapering off any?
- I don't wanna use the word tapering off.
It's lighter than it
was about 20 minutes ago
here in Arlington, but it's
still raining a good amount.
I don't know if you can see
it off the umbrella here.
It's still coming down at a good clip.
Not torrential, the way we
saw it in Boyds this morning
and as we came down the I-270
corridor into the beltway,
but again, still a
tremendous amount of rain.
You can probably see it on
top of the standing water.
The drops falling on the standing water,
so that gives you an idea of just
how much rain we're still
getting, Veronica, in this area.
Again, these gentlemen here
trying to help this lady,
Veronica, were gonna try to
move the car on their own
and good thing they didn't,
because that's never a good idea.
- Yeah, Johnny, that is
actually just an amazing shot.
Of course, we've seen some
other water rescues going on
across the area similar to that.
Wanna go ahead and, if we
can split the screen again
and put the video back up,
because one thing I want you to know.
I was in Ellicott City, Maryland,
for both flash flood events,
flash flood emergency events.
That's why it's called flash flooding,
because it can occur in
a flash, where you have
that much water that
accumulates so quickly.
That shot not as dramatic as the shot
that we were just seeing
there with Johnny Gonzalez,
but again, that's the reason
that we call it flash flooding;
where the water comes up in
a hurry has nowhere to go.
Especially if you're in an area,
if you're traveling through an area
or if you live in an area
with a lot of concrete,
the ground cannot pick up that water.
It cannot take in that water and you know,
we've had six back-to-back
days with heavy rain
during the afternoon with
some of these summer storms.
Well, there's a look at the capital wheel.
Again, you're saying what capital wheel?
Where is it?
It's on the far, left-hand
portion of your screen,
really hard to see as heavy rain continues
through the nation's capital,
here in the Capital Metro area
and there's a look, in
fact, of the Capitol dome.
You're seeing just a little bit of it
in the distance there
in that bright white.
What typically is morning
for us where by this time
we can see a little better,
over the last hour and
a half to two hours,
we've seen that heavy rain
make its way through the area.
Here's a look at Clarksburg Road.
This is I-270, where some
of the heaviest has already
come through, but I betcha if
you're in northern, western
Montgomery County, you're
probably still seeing the creeks,
streams all still continue
to come up across the area.
Here's a look at the radar loop.
You heard Johnny Gonzalez
say where he was this morning
up in Frederick County, Maryland.
This is where he was earlier.
He's really traveled with
that line down to the south
into the metro area,
now just south and east
about ready to pull into portions
of northern Charles County.
Look at Dunkirk, still some
lightening with that near 301
and south of Bowie, so we may
see improvement conditions
to the north here around
Damascus, around Gaithersburg,
Laurel, Ellicott City, but
still down to the south,
where those flash flood warnings continue
and flash flood emergency
all the way south now
into Charles County just
past noon today until 1 p.m.,
we'll continue to have that
threat of flash flooding.
Let's go back to Johnny Gonzalez,
who has more on that water rescue.
- And Veronica, we're
seeing some progress.
Just in the last few minutes, an update.
You can see the Hundai Elantra
here is now out of the water
but well, you can see it's
got some drying out to do.
This car was almost completely
submerged when we arrived,
the driver telling us that the car
was parked here on
Kennebec Street and 11th.
She saw the water starting to pick up
and she tried to move it but
she didn't have enough time
and this gentleman here, Mike, came by
in his Ford F-150.
You didn't get called,
you just happened to come across this.
- No, I was running an errand this morning
and I got caught in it and I
was stuck in traffic everywhere
and then I figured I'd be close to home
and then I saw them locked up
and I always say it's not bad weather,
it's bad preparation, so you
always got the gear with you,
got the frog togs and just
decided to cruise around
and see if there is anything
I can do in my neighborhood.
- You made pretty quick work of this.
How dangerous is something like this,
when you have folks that may be driving.
We saw a guy try to get
through something like this.
You seem like you're maybe
more experienced than others
in a situation like this.
How dangerous can this be?
- Well, you know, there's
always a risk when you're trying
to ford a river or any
sort of standing water
and it's, around here, I
figured I know the landscape
pretty well, I know
how deep the roads are.
You can see some certain points,
like halfway up a fire hydrant
might only be a couple feet deep,
so you can use some sort of inferences
to know how deep it is,
but it's always a risk.
Unless you have a larger
vehicle, I wouldn't recommend it,
especially with some of the smaller,
low-profile sedans and whatnot.
- Mike, thanks so much and again, thanks
for helping this young
lady get out of the water.
John, if you pan the
camera, you can see her now
trying to collect some of
her personal belongings
that literally floated out of the vehicle
and even in the last couple of
minutes since we last talked,
Veronica, you can see what I said earlier.
These...been talking
about the flash flooding
and as quickly as it comes
through, the water recedes.
In about 10 minutes, there's
not gonna be any problem here.
You're gonna see, not a dry
road, but no standing water
and that's what's amazing
about a situation like this.
That quickly, in just a matter of minutes,
you can find yourself in a big problem
and again, you have vehicles
at the top of the hill here
on Kennebec trying to,
well, they're attempting,
but that vehicle there, the
black SUV doing the smart thing,
turning around, and that
white vehicle, there you go.
You don't wanna try to
cross something like this
because it just takes a matter of seconds
to get yourself in a lot of trouble.
Veronica, back to you inside.
- That's right and that's
why on days when we talk
about the possibility of
flash flooding, when we say
that the area is under
a flash flood watch,
that's when you need to
prepare early in the day
and that's why it's a good idea
to stay with Storm Watch 7,
always have that Storm Watch
7 weather app ready to go.
Make sure the notifications are turned on
because should there be
a flash flood emergency,
you bet my phone went off
this morning several times
with all the warnings and
emergencies that we already had.
So how much longer, again,
until two, 3 p.m. today,
big story today is that heavy
rain, that very heavy rain
that will continue to
move through our area.
I've put on a couple of amounts here
in terms of rainfall of
what we've seen already.
Look at Addison Height,
2.4 inches of rain.
2.8 inches of rain just
south of Hall's Hill area
and just north of McLean,
close to 5 inches of rain.
Again, this not in a 12- or 24-hour period
a lot of times when we show those amounts,
but this in an hour to an hour and a half.
So all that rain comes up very quickly,
comes out of the storm
drains where the storm drains
can't take the water, so
it just sits on the road
and increases very quickly.
Just in a foot of road, can
start to carry your car away
in two feet of water very easily.
So that much water, don't ever attempt
to drive across a flooded road.
Look at western portions
of Montgomery County
there around Rockville.
This is just west of
270, 3.4 inches of rain.
These are some of the totals throughout
and this loop over the last three hours,
we're doing a little better
here in Loudoun County.
In Montgomery County,
you heard Johnny Gonzalez
just mention how things
are starting to improve.
The water starting to recede,
but it'll take some time
perhaps for the creeks,
the rivers, the streams,
if you live anywhere there.
I know your kids out of school today.
Maybe they're not at summer camp.
Make sure they're not in the
backyard playing near those
if you live in some of
these areas, 'cause again,
we've already had a
number of water rescues.
Your heaviest rain now with
some lightening right here,
coming through Prince George's
County, right around 301,
crossing over, making its way very slowly
to the east and southeast,
so soon Waldorf, soon Dunkirk
and eventually Prince
Frederick, making its way
south from Bowie and south of Annapolis,
you folks doing a bit better.
So we're gonna see improving
conditions on area roads,
but that too is going to take awhile.
Heavy rain now, Alexandria
south to Mount Vernon.
That's right down Route One.
Some heavy rain too around areas of 301.
This is south of Silver Hill
and down toward the Clinton
area and Franconia, so if you
live in these areas, stay put.
Treat it just as you would a
severe thunderstorm warning
or for that matter, any
elevated, severe warning
that we get on the air and issue for you.
This is kind of a life and death
situation with so much rain
that is falling across the area.
For Howard County, you stay under that
flash flood warning until 11:45.
That's western portions of Howard County
but even around Ellicott City and east
toward Catonsville or up toward Baltimore.
Probably still some ponding on area roads.
Then right down the south
through the District.
That's Bowie, that's down
toward Charles County.
That is where all this is going.
Again, very slowly.
This whole again started three hours ago
and we're still dealing with
a heavy rain across the area.
So lets talk about what's next for us.
That is maybe some improving visibility
by the time we get to noon.
Right now it's at a
mile and a half in D.C.
Just a couple minutes ago,
I was on the air showing you
a half mile and it's improved
to Joint Base Andrews,
right now down at a half mile visibility.
So throughout the day
today, we're gonna stay
on a weather alert at least until noon,
maybe one, two o'clock
before improving conditions.
That rain isn't probably gonna end
until about three, four o'clock.
The rain easing and then
eventually clearing.
So again, the very latest is
several flash flood emergencies
continue across the area.
I know, Steve Rudin, you're
standing by with more
on some of the rainfall
totals and what's happening
on social media right now.
- Yeah and VJ, before we get to see,
we wanna show you, everybody's
been talking about this rain
and they've been tweeting
out some amazing pictures,
so let's take a look
at some of the flooding
that we're seeing around our region,
and over on the right side of your screen,
it looks like we got a
picture of an interstate there
and it's just a wet mess.
Here, you can see a closer
up picture with some ponding
and where is this exactly?
- [Adriana] This is Sam Sweeney's pictures
that he's tweeting out on social media.
You can follow him at sweeneyabc.
Basically, this is right outside of Dulles
and the FAA has already sent
out a tweet to everyone,
letting people know that
if you're flying out,
check your flight times
because they could be delayed.
Several areas right now
dealing with some bad weather,
from Miami and Fort Lauderdale
all the way up north to LaGuardia.
Reagan and Dulles, the FAA
says, could have some delays
because of this weather.
But this is what you're
seeing around Dulles.
Just the flash flooding
and the flooding there
and Steve, you were
talking just a minute ago
while Veronica was updating
everyone in terms of the radar.
How much rain have we
seen and in how much time?
- There have been jackpot
zones and Veronica and I
have been showing you all
morning long those jackpot zones
in Arlington, over toward
McLean, over toward Potomac.
Then you head over into
eastern Montgomery County,
where not as much rain has fallen,
but upwards of two to four inches,
that is the safe bet right now,
but I would not be surprised...