(energetic music)
- [Narrator] Stay ahead of the storms
with the StormWatch7 app.
(ominous music)
- [Announcer] It's the Fourth of July.
And, Kelly and Ryan are having a party.
A pool party.
Today, here to splash
in the pretend water,
the guys from "Stranger Things."
And, you can't have a
celebration without music.
So, O.A.R is here,
as our holiday house band.
And, the co-hosts are tossing bags
with the American Cornhole Champions.
Plus, members of our studio audience
could win some holiday prizes
when they compete in our
Fourth of July Games.
All next, on Live.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
And now, here are your
All-American co-hosts,
Kelly Ripa and Ryan Seacrest.
(audience applauding and cheering)
- Hey!
Woo! Looking good!
Hi!
- Hi.
(upbeat dance music)
(audience applauding and cheering)
- Happy Fourth of July.
Good morning, everybody.
(audience applauding and cheering)
Welcome to our party!
- Hey, guess what?
O.A.R is our
house band today, baby.
- Yeah, yeah.
- They're going to be performing for us
throughout the show, thank you.
- Kelly, please.
- Look at this.
(applause)
- Let's talk about the
Fourth of July, Kelly.
- Ryan, I was hoping
you would bring it up.
(audience laughs)
- The most important part of the Fourth,
obviously, is not necessarily the history,
but posting photographs of your
celebration on this day, right?
- Correct.
- So many great opportunities.
- Now--
- Sophia, you are so cute.
Sorry, go ahead.
- These are the best
captions for Fourth of July,
for your pictures.
So, you're welcome.
Put these to good use later.
Drinkin', #DrinkinLikeLincoln.
(audience laughs)
(cheering and applause)
Now I'm not making these up.
These are actually online.
Um...
Red, White, and Brew.
#RedWhiteAndBrew.
(applause and cheering)
The Star Spangled Hammered.
(laughing)
(audience cheers)
Sippin' On LiberTea.
- Yeah, I like that.
- Well, that's...
If you want.
(audience member laughing)
- Mhm.
You know what?
- Tell me, Kel.
- It's funny,
- Is it?
We're talking about,
where can we keep this gigantic flamingo?
Because, we can all agree,
this is probably the greatest
pool float in the universe.
- [Audience Member] Oh, yeah!
(applause and cheering)
- I think so.
- Seaworthy.
This is like the yacht of sea,
of pool floats,
Would you not say?
- This is it.
- This is what you
(stammers) strive for.
- You guys are rock stars.
You have this all day long.
This is like, in your tub.
(laughing)
But, would you like to see
the world's largest pool?
It's at a resort in Chile.
- [Ryan] Look at that, oh my God.
- [Kelly] It's the San Alfonso Del Mar.
World's largest man-made lagoon.
It's the exact same crystal-clear,
turquoise hue of the sea.
- Sea Water.
- So, they made the pool
look just like the sea,
and they filled it with sea water.
I mean, why not just go in the sea, right?
I mean, am I right?
- Well, listen,
- [Kelly] Am I just...
- But, listen--
- Am I just being a killjoy?
- [Ryan] A lot of people
are afraid of, I don't know.
What they have in the sea.
They could have jellyfish.
They could have other animals,
creatures...
- Well listen,
somebody goes over there,
- This is safe.
- Grabs something over there,
and pulls a prank,
and throws it in the pool.
It's gonna live,
because it's sea water.
- It's gonna live
'cause it's sea water.
- Right?
- Honey, I'll be right back.
I'm going to do some laps.
- Yeah.
How long do you think
that would take, days?
- I guess.
I mean, they've got sailboats in there.
But, we could definitely get
a whole flock of these flamingos.
- Yeah.
(audience laughs)
We could jet ski in there.
- Yeah.
- If that's legal.
- I see all kinds of things in there.
- Sometimes, by the way,
you know, there are some people
who are afraid to swim in the ocean,
and so that's a good alternative.
On the Fourth of July,
we should tell you,
I mean, you know this,
obviously from history.
United States observes a federal holiday,
in honor of the Declaration
of Independence.
Commemorates the adoption of the
Declaration of Independence,
July 4th, 1776.
(audience applause and cheering)
By delegates from the 13 colonies.
Now, now the important stuff.
If the Fourth of July falls on a Sunday,
we observe the holiday
on the following Monday.
If it falls on a Saturday,
we observe it on a Friday.
- If it falls on a Thursday--
- If it falls on a Tuesday,
we take the whole rest
of the week off.
- Exactly.
(audience laughs)
If it falls in between...
(audience applause)
- Hey, did you hear about this?
- No, but I'm about to.
(audience members laugh)
- Do you guys know, how many--
Let's see, I see a lot of
young people here today.
Millennials, and Gen Z'ers,
- Hey guys.
- Where are you?
Yes.
(audience cheers)
Lots.
- My people.
- Your people are here.
- Your people are
representing.
- That's right, I see you.
- So, the flamingo pose is the latest
Instagram friendly stance.
Do you know about the
flamingo pose, everybody?
- Oh.
(audience murmurs)
- Here's, I believe,
is that Kendall Jenner?
Yep, Kendall Jenner is...
Well, are they calling
it the flamingo pose
because she's wearing that dress?
Or, because her legs, the one leg?
- Well, the dress helps.
- Gelman, we are,
you know, we are in
our thong shorts,
- Yes.
- So, maybe you can do
the flamingo for us?
(audience hollering)
- Maybe.
- Somehow that
looks different.
That doesn't look like...
(audience laughs)
- [Ryan] That was tree, from yoga.
- (laughs) Well that's all I--
- Yeah.
- You stand on one leg,
and you get bonus points,
if you can slightly cross your knees.
Which helps to create a
slimming effect for your legs.
- [Ryan] Let's see your bonus points.
(audience laughs)
- Gelman, you've got--
- What about my knee?
- Well, I wouldn't want--
- Come on.
What do you want from me?
- You're actually--
- He actually looks--
- Alright.
The other thing that's
a trend this summer...
(stammers) This is not good for your skin.
Can't highly recommend it.
But, they're saying sunburn tattoos.
You know when you fall asleep in the sun,
you leave your hand like this?
- Yes.
- Anybody?
- Yeah.
- So, sunburn tattoos
are big for the Summer of 2019.
People are placing
stencils on exposed skin.
Soaking up the sun.
And then, they've got,
you know, the Batman logo,
or other different things
- Oh, geeze.
- That look like a tattoo.
- [Kelly] Oh, that seems dangerous though.
- It's, well that's not--
I mean, and you know it's not,
here's the thing kids,
and I'm going to tell you this...
(clears throat)
Oh, gosh.
(audience laughs)
Here's what I'm going to tell you,
because nobody told us,
in my day, this.
Because, there was still like,
a lot of conflicting data
about sunscreen
- Mmm, mhm.
- At least in our household.
- Right.
- It's not the sunburn that day, right?
It's what the sunburn turns into,
30 years from now.
- Ah.
- Right, moms?
Yeah.
- So put it on
early so--
- And, I know that it is
in your instinct, Sophia,
to tune out the moms.
Do you understand?
I get it.
We get it.
It's everybody's instinct
to tune out the moms,
- To tune out the moms.
Right.
- But, we actually,
(stammers) we actually,
when it comes to this thing,
know exactly what we're
talking about.
- You carry wisdom with this.
- Yes, you don't need,
you don't need a Batman shaped melanoma,
30 years from now.
(laughing)
(applause)
(audience hollering)
- One other quick public service
for the barbecuers today,
for July 4th.
- Yes?
- If you are someone that--
When I'm out, and I'm with other people,
usually they get the mosquito bites.
- Am I crowding you?
I just noticed you leaned away from me.
I feel like...
I feel like I just brushed my teeth.
So, I don't think it's a--
- No, no, no.
You smell like a lozenge.
- I do.
Well, that's because I ate the lozenge.
- No, but you're not crowding me at all.
- Right.
- I just wanted to make
eye contact.
- Oh, okay.
So, your vision is going?
- My vision's bad.
Kelly?
- Kay.
- Kelly?
- You're the first millennial
I've ever seen do that.
(laughing)
- Can I borrow my millennial
glasses to read this?
- Sure, go for it.
- Oh, look at this!
No, it's a public service.
So, usually I'm not the one
gets eaten by mosquitoes.
It's the person I'm with.
Which is a great going out benefit, but...
- Oh my gosh.
- If you're the one
that always gets the mosquito bites,
researches say, music by Skrillex
will prevent the
mosquitoes from biting you.
(audience laughs)
Researchers examined the effects
of electronic music on mosquitoes,
and it made 'em less likely to bite.
- Yay Skrillex.
- So, Skrillex is
the soundtrack to your barbecue.
Today on the show,
the cast of "Stranger
Things," they are here.
(audience applauding and cheering)
Gaten, Finn, Caleb, Noah,
they're all here, backstage.
A whole bunch of 'em.
(laughing)
- And, nothing says Fourth
of July like cornhole.
So, we're gonna play cornhole
with the top competitors
from the American Cornhole League.
By the way...
(audience cheering)
(audience applauding)
I was like,
I thought we called it,
on our show, live-hole.
And, they were like,
no, it's only live-hole
when we throw the beanbags
into our mouths.
- Into your--
Exactly.
- Yes.
- We've special game that we developed.
- Unbelievable.
- This is the real game.
- This is the real--
- This is the league?
- Cornhole.
- We have the
league champions, alright.
And, throughout today's show,
members of our studio
audience will play Live's
Fourth of July games.
The first game is our
annual Fourth of July
trivia dancer-off.
The dancers dressed themselves up.
They're ready to try and
dance their way to victory.
So, let's dance.
(audience applauding and cheering)
- First up, say hello to Mary Malloy.
From East Rockaway, New York.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
- There she is.
Our next contestant is Gary Callione,
from Cincinnati, Ohio, Gar!
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
What's up, my brother?
- Nice, Gary!
Our third contestant is Carla Gomen,
from El Dorado Hills, California.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
Very nice.
- And, the last,
but not least,
let's bring out Meredith Miller,
from San Antonio, Texas.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
- Alright, studio audience.
You have a job.
- Oh, yes.
- You're going to vote
for your favorite dancer,
and after trivia,
we will announce who the
audience picked to win.
- [Man] Alright!
- Alright, yeah.
- Okay?
(audience applauding and cheering)
(Kelly mumbles)
- These are cool.
- Thanks.
- I love those.
- They're not mine,
they're Jan's.
- Oh.
Well Jan, those are great.
- Thank you.
- All week long, we're playing a special
audience edition of "Stump The Hosts,"
Where an audience shares a
summer-themed truth or lie,
and we have to figure out which is verdad.
- If they stump us,
they get a Kelly and Ryan mug,
and a $1,200 kitchen appliance
package, from Cuisinart,
which we can all agree,
is all of the kitchen appliances.
- It is everything.
So dancers, give it your all, right now.
It's time for "Stump the
Hosts," audience edition.
♪ Da-da, doo-doo ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
♪ Gonna be okay ♪
♪ Da-Da, doo-doo ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
♪ Spin that record, babe ♪
♪ Da-da, doo-doo ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
♪ Gonna be okay ♪
♪ Just, just, just dance ♪
♪ Dance, dance ♪
♪ J-J-Just dance ♪
(upbeat dance music)
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ Half psychotic, sick, hypnotic ♪
♪ Got my blueprint, it's symphonic ♪
♪ Got my blueprint electronic ♪
♪ Half psychotic, sick, hypnotic ♪
(audience applauding and cheering)
Aright, okay.
- Now, that's what I call
U-S-of-Yay, am I right?
- Yeah you are.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Happy Independence Day!
- Good job, you four, amazing.
Now, let's meet today's
audience participant.
Where is Holly Dance, from Ogden, Utah?
- Holly Dance?
- Hi, Holly!
(audience applauding and cheering)
(Kelly giggles)
Okay.
- Okay.
- Okay, you can stay
right there in the ocean.
- Okay.
- And, Ryan and I
will stay here on this side of the
tail end of the flamingo.
- Awesome.
- Okay.
- So, by the way,
happy Fourth of July.
- Thank you, so much.
- You look great!
- Thank you, thank you.
- Yeah, you look adorable.
- [Ryan] What is your first statement?
- My first statement is that every summer,
my family and I,
we have a friend who's in marketing,
and we get a billboard,
a vinyl billboard,
rip the whole thing down,
put it down the hill,
in their backyard,
and we water-slide down the billboard.
- Ooh!
- Oh, that sounds like fun.
- You steal the billboard
from--
- No, he's in marketing.
So, they're old billboards.
- They're old, so it's fine.
Okay, and what's your second
- Yeah.
- Statement?
- My second statement is that
every Fourth of July,
my husband and I are in the town parade,
and we're a husband and
wife real-estate team.
So, I dressed up as the Statue of Liberty,
and we have a big American flag,
and we throw out candy in the parade.
- [Ryan] But, he's in
marketing, I thought?
- No, a friend is
in marketing.
- Oh.
Well, let's see what the
audience thinks on this.
- I don't know.
You've got an honest face.
- I am honest.
- You do.
Sliding down the vinyl billboard.
- Huh.
- So, you put water on it?
- Yeah, we get a hose
and put it at the top--
- Do you use soap?
Like a liquid soap?
- Yep, we get dish
soap at the top,
and the kids all squirt
it down the top.
- That sounds dangerous.
Like, you could really hurt yourselves.
- That sounds fun.
- Even on the Slip N Slide.
Right? Don't they say adults
- It's a grass hill.
Over the age of 12,
and if you weigh more
than blah, blah, blah.
- [Holly] It's a grass hill.
- It's a grass hill?
I like that story.
- Okay.
- What do you think?
- I think that that's...
Okay, I'm gonna...
I don't wanna...
It's the Fourth of July.
So, for the sake of harmony,
- Yeah?
- I'm gonna go with you.
But, in the back of my mind,
I want it noted,
that I actually believe that is B.S..
Okay?
(audience laughs)
- In the name of harmony,
is it true that you
slide down the billboard?
- Am I supposed to tell you
right now?
- Yes, right now.
- Yes, it's true.
- Yay!
(laughing)
(audience applauding and cheering)
- Happy holiday.
- Wow.
- Thank you, audience.
Thank you.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Now you, and a lucky member
of our studio audience,
will each receive a $500 gift card
from World Market.
- Ah!
Yeah!
Fourth of July.
- Fish bowl.
- Huh?
Oh, fish bowl.
- Right here.
- Yeah, sorry.
- I got your tickets,
everybody.
- There's nothing like doing
this show like it's
the first time.
- Like it's...
We've ever done it.
- Even though it's my 9,000th show.
Uh...
40, number 40.
- Number 40.
(audience cheering)
- Yeah!
- Right there?
(audience applauding and cheering)
- [Woman] Woo!
(Kelly laughs)
- Happy Fourth.
Thank you so much,
- Thank you.
- For being here.
- Thank you, very much.
Thanks.
- Let's see.
Now, dim the light, because...
- Oh, is this where
- Oh, this is exciting.
- We reveal the winning
dancer?
- The results.
- Oh my gosh.
- Of our dance-off are in.
(dramatic drum roll)
The person voted as this year's winner,
and getting a $500 gift
certificate to Omaha Steaks,
is...
We'll find out, after the break.
(audience laughs)
- Just kidding, calm down.
- It is, Carla!
Carla, from El Dorado Hills, California.
(audience applauding and cheering)
Good job, Carla.
(murmuring)
- That's good spirit.
Thank you for playing.
- Thank you, very much
for playing along, great job.
- And, Happy Fourth of July.
- Coming up next, the
cast of "Stranger Things."
We're right back, on the Fourth.
(audience applauding and cheering)
Just, whatever.
- I know, it's like...
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Still ahead, on Live,
O.A.R will perform their latest hit.
We continue to celebrate Independence Day
with Fourth of July games,
when more lucky members
of our studio audience
will win more prizes.
We'll play cornhole with
the league champions.
Coming up next,
the cast of "Stranger Things."
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] For mild to moderate eczema,
Eucrisa can be used almost everywhere.
On almost every body.
Like the hands of a hair stylist.
Or the calf of a cutie.
Prescription Eucrisa works at, and below,
the surface of the skin.
It blocks overactive PDE4 enzymes.
Which is believed to reduce inflammation.
- And, it's steroid free.
- [Narrator] Do not use if
you are allergic to Eucrisa,
or it's ingredients.
Allergic reactions may occur
at or near the application site.
The most common side effect
is application site pain.
Ask your doctor about Eucrisa.
- [Cat] Look, a door to another demen--
Oh no, just a bag.
- [Cat] Train insane,
or remain the same.
(sighs)
- [Narrator] We'll never
totally figure them out,
but we do know what makes them happy.
Meow Mix.
40 years, and still the only
one cats ask for by name.
- [Narrator] This is you shopping.
And this, is you maximizing.
At TJ Maxx.
Get more of the brands you love,
and quality you want.
And, save every time.
It's not shopping, it's maximizing.
Max live, at TJ Maxx.
- [Narrator] When someone's on your side,
you feel like everything is gonna be okay.
And, it will be.
Seven's on your side to
inform, alert, advocate,
and lend a helping hand.
ABC7 News, always on your side.
- [Narrator] At La-Z-Boy
Furniture Galleries,
we know everyone has their favorite spot.
It's the Fourth of July sale.
Save on reclines from $399,
plus get 30% off everything else.
La-Z-Boy Furniture Galleries,
live life comfortably.
- [Narrator] WJLA maintains
quarterly children's
television reports in its public file.
The public file is available
for review by the public, at WJLA.com.
Click on FCC Info.
(adventurous music)
- [Narrator] Storm Watch 7.
Seven strong.
On a mission.
- Knowing where the threat is.
Knowing how's it's going to impact you.
That makes all the difference.
- [Narrator] Storm Watch 7,
seven strong,
and always on your side.
(eccentric music)
- Now.
(robots humming)
(dramatic wailing)
(squawkers humming)
(hysteric screams)
(can sprays)
(screaming)
(audience applauding and cheering)
(giggling)
- He's scared already.
Here come four of the
young residents of the
twisted television town
of Hawkins, Indiana.
From the hit series, "Stranger Things,"
please welcome Finn
Wolfhard, Noah Schnapp,
Caleb McLaughlin, and Gaten Matarazzo.
(audience applauding and cheering)
(exciting music)
Hi.
Come on in, come on in.
- Come on.
(Ryan murmurs)
- Hi, Finn.
How are you?
(Kelly murmurs)
(muffled crosstalk)
(exciting music)
Have a seat.
- Come on in.
- Hi, (murmurs)
Hi, I'm Kelly.
- Alright.
- That's a way (mumbles).
Yeah, I said that.
(Ryan mumbles)
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
(muffled crosstalk)
- [Kelly] Yeah, sit on the cushions there.
- Yeah--
- (mumbles) Celebration.
(grunts)
- This shouldn't be awkward at all.
- No.
- This is--
- It's actually quite comfy.
- Yeah.
- Isn't it nice?
- What do you think of this?
Now, you guys--
Listen,
- Oh my God,
this is so cool.
- You guys are
Hollywood stars.
You must have these
falling out of the sky.
- That's right.
- Yeah, it's on our rider.
- So, where is everyone from?
Let's see.
- We're from the,
New York City, the Big Apple.
- You're from the Big Apple.
Okay.
- New York City.
Born and raised?
- Yes.
Born and raised.
- Alright.
- And, Finn's from Vancouver,
right?
- I'm from Vancouver.
- What about you?
- I'm from,
my whole family from Montreal,
but I'm from New York.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- Fab.
- Jersey.
- Come on.
- Oh, there you go.
- She knew--
- I don't wanna show,
I don't wanna show favorites,
I'm just saying.
- It's all good, I understand.
- People from Jersey
understand each other,
that's all.
- It's okay.
New York is better,
- 'Cause no one else
- But it's okay.
- Understands us.
- Nobody else--
(muffled crosstalk)
- Our families are both from Canada,
so, we're nicer.
- Yeah.
- Well, you're more polite.
You're more polite.
- Now that you guys have worked together
for a few seasons,
I'm sure you get to know each other.
Like, I know what--
You can't get under her skin,
but I know what can wind Kelly up.
- Like what?
What's one thing that can wind me up?
- Serving you garlic.
- Oh, that is true.
- Oh, yeah.
- You put garlic
in any of her food--
- I love garlic.
- You do?
- Me too.
I love it too.
- Really?
- Oh, it's awesome.
- I'm very sensitive to it.
- Very sensitive to garlic.
- Oh.
- Do you guys know little
things about each other now?
Or, do you like the--
- I thought you were about
to ask us if we knew
anything about garlic.
(laughing)
I was like um, well.
- Caleb's always blowing his nose.
All the time.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- Every day of his life.
- You know why?
I have PTSD as a child.
- Okay.
- I look at old pictures of my young self,
and there's a lot of boogers.
So, I...
(laughing)
I also...
- Yeah.
- I suffer from that,
and I'm like,
I make sure there is
no boogers in my nose.
- Wait, do you--
- So...
- Caleb, do you have like,
boogers--
- So, every time I feel
something, I'm like--
- Older siblings?
- Yeah, I do.
But, they won't tell me.
- They didn't tell you.
- Nah.
- That's right, yeah.
- You should have people
on the set that tell you
whether you have boogers--
- Oh, they do.
- They do.
- But, I just,
when I feel something,
I'm like, can I get a tissue?
- Yeah, it's not there.
- There is also--
- Kelly loves a snot rocket.
She just (whistles), fires it right out.
- Well, it comes to the
point where it's like,
we're doing a really serious scene,
and Caleb's off camera,
- Oh, yeah.
- And I'm like doing,
and I'm doing the scene,
I look at Caleb, and he's like--
(laughing)
As quietly as he can.
- Every picture of myself
as a three-year-old child,
it's just shiny boogers.
- Oh, that's with every kid.
- Delicious.
- We've been doing scenes...
- We've been doing scenes,
and like, the camera will be on one of us,
and like, he'll be behind the camera,
reading for us,
and he'll just be blowing his nose
during the middle of the shot.
I'm like dude, really?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- And then, it makes me laugh so much.
Like, when the cameras--
- It makes me laugh so much.
- Well, what does Gaten do?
Finn, what does Gaten do?
- Uh...
- He's perfect.
He's from New Jersey.
- A lot.
- Gaten...
- Gaten does like--
- Yeah, Gaten does a lot.
- Gaten just dances (mumbles).
- He dances, and sings a lot.
- He's always (mumbles).
- Well, 'cause he's happy.
He's from New Jersey.
- I'm happy.
- That's great.
- Jersey's not happy.
- Jersey--
- Yes, yes.
- [Noah] Are all people
from New Jersey happy?
- Yes, we're all happy.
- No (laughs).
- We are, listen, we are happy.
And, if you question us,
- We're happier,
- We will fight you about it.
- And we're nicer.
- That's how happy we are.
- Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
- We are intense.
- We will beat you up,
- We will fight you about it.
- Over how happy we are.
- Now, who has
their driver's license among you?
- Oh.
- I have my permit.
- No on has it.
- Good question.
- I have my permit.
- You're permitted?
- Yeah, I get my license in September.
- Oh, you do?
- Are you excited?
- Yeah, I am excited.
- And, I get my license
when I turn 18.
- When you turn 18?
- Yeah, this year, this year.
- Yeah, okay.
- I'm 14 years (mumbles).
- You're 14!
- But, I can get my (mumbles).
- Go-karts. I got a...
I went in for the first
learners-permit test,
really excited,
and I got (stammers),
I didn't get every question wrong,
but...
(laughing)
(stammers) It's why I chose
acting over academics,
and...
(laughing)
And, I got one question wrong.
It was like the passing thing,
(stammers) I like, just
like, held my head low,
and like, I got up,
and my mom was like, "Did you pass?"
And, I was just like, "Let's go."
- You know what?
- Listen--
(Kelly stammers)
- We'll be fine.
- Get chauffeurs.
You're on a hit show
- Yeah.
- For God sakes.
- I wanna drive.
(muffled crosstalk)
(audience applauding and cheering)
- Is everyone a chauffeur,
in the audience?
We got a chauffeur's
audience.
- Yeah.
Well, we--
- Now that I'm
finally driving, I don't
like being a passenger.
At all.
- Oh.
- 'Cause, you wanna be in control?
- I do.
- Backseat driver.
- It's weird.
I'm not a backseat driver.
I try not to be.
It was funny, my uncle,
my mom's twin brother,
told her, when she first started driving,
'cause he got his license first,
that if there was a white
line around a stop sign,
it was optional.
- What?
(laughing)
- That's really funny.
- And, for those of you
who don't know,
I'm sure most of you do,
- That's very funny.
- Most stop signs have a
white line around them.
And, it took her like,
three months to realize that was not true.
- So, how many stop signs
did she run?
- No one was hurt.
No one was hurt.
Everyone was fine.
- Nobody was hurt.
I love that.
- So, you guys are
on this massively popular
show, "Stranger Things."
- I'm like, falling.
- That's alright,
there's a hole there.
- I know.
There's a hole we designed.
- We created.
- Yeah.
Just lean back, and relax.
Yeah, come on.
- Is it difficult
to keep the secrets of the show?
- Is it difficult to keep--
- Because, people are always
wanting to know what's coming up,
what's happening, right?
- I feel like, nowadays,
because we're in season three,
in the beginning it wasn't so hard,
because nothing was out.
But now, I forget which
season I'm talking about.
- Yeah, same.
- And then,
I might spoil something.
- Right.
- Or, say something about
the season that's coming out.
But, no one catches it.
- In season one,
we told everybody like,
the entire plot line.
- Yeah.
- Was spoiling everything.
- Well, we were like,
okay, so like,
- Yeah (laughs).
- (stammers) There's
this girl named Eleven,
and then at the end,
she disappears.
- Yeah.
Everybody's like, good show.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Good luck with that.
- We were telling everybody.
- Yeah, and then we were like,
yeah, that was probably it.
Like, whatever.
- But, you do realize that
you are portraying the greatest time
in the history of time,
the '80s.
- The '80s.
- Yeah.
- Like, our parents are always
telling us that they love it.
- Your parents are
literally telling you what
it was like during--
- Yeah, my parents relate
to everything that like,
the towels that we have,
or, not the towels,
our shirts like,
have like towel material.
- Yes, of course.
- Terry cloth.
- They wore that.
- Towel material.
That was so cute.
- That was adorable.
My kids, for the first time,
saw a wall phone,
(laughing)
on "Stranger Things,"
and they said,
"What is that thing--"
(muffled crosstalk)
They had never seen a wall phone.
- There's like, a whole bunch in
New York City.
- Okay, I doubt,
before you did "Stranger Things,"
if you really think back--
- I knew what a rotary phone--
- Hey, Jersey,
calm down, you two.
- I knew what a
rotary phone was.
- Listen, I will--
- We're gonna take a break.
Coming up, things get
strange when the guys
play a hands-on guessing game,
right after this.
Stay with us.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
- [Announcer] Still ahead, on Live,
A performance by house band, O.A.R.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
(illuminating music)
- My body is truly powerful.
- I have the power to lower
my blood-sugar and A1C.
- I guess I can still make my own insulin,
and Trulicity activates my body,
to release it
like it's supposed to.
- [Narrator] Trulicity is for
people with type 2 diabetes.
It's not insulin.
- [Man] I take it once a week.
It starts acting in my
body from the first dose.
- [Narrator] Trulicity isn't for
people with type 1 diabetes,
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Don't take Trulicity if
you're allergic to it,
you or your family have
medullary thyroid cancer,
or have multiple endocrine
neoplasia syndrome type 2.
Stop Trulicity and call
your doctor right away
if you have an allergic reaction,
a lump or swelling in your neck,
or severe stomach pain.
Serious side effects may
include pancreatitis.
Taking Trulicity with a
sulfonylurea, or insulin,
increases low-blood-sugar risk.
Side effects include nausea,
diarrhea, vomiting, belly
pain, and decreased appetite,
which lead to dehydration,
and may worsen kidney problems.
- I have it within me to lower my A1C.
- [Narrator] Ask your
doctor about Trulicity.
(cars driving past)
- How would I describe
overpaying on a used car?
It's humiliating!
And, It's expensive!
I just trusted the wrong used car sites.
(grunts)
- CARFAX has a better way.
Only carfax.com can give
you the most accurate price,
based on the CARFAX report.
So, you never have to
overpay on a used car again.
- But, I guess life goes on.
So, aright, come on, boy.
Here we go.
Let's go, buddy.
(dog barks)
- Stop the shame of overpaying,
and start your used car search today,
at the all-new carfax.com.
♪ One, two ♪
(record scratching)
(crunch)
(air whooshing)
♪ One, two ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Give me a break ♪
♪ Break me off a piece
of that Kit-Kat bar ♪
(gentle music)
- [Narrator] Marlo
Furniture's July 4th sale.
Time to declare your independence
from boring furniture.
With 60% savings on every living room
Every dining room.
Every bedroom.
60% savings.
Plus, free delivery.
Plus, up to 60 months
zero-interest financing.
Plus, when you buy a mattress at Marlo,
we'll donate one to a
homeless veterans shelter.
Marlo Furniture's July 4th sale.
Upgrade your home,
help a homeless veteran.
Now, that's worth celebrating.
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
(uplifting music)
♪ Alright ♪
(crowd cheering)
♪ Here we go, now ♪
♪ Give a little bit of my love to you ♪
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
- "Stranger Things."
"Stranger Things" three,
available today, on Netflix.
Today, today, today.
- Today is the day.
- I'm sure people have already binged
the entire season.
- Done.
- While we sat here on the show,
but we are back,
with the cast of "Stranger Things."
And, everybody here is
gonna participate in a game
of "What's in the box?"
Woo.
(crowd applauding)
For this challenge,
Ryan and the boys,
are gonna reach into
- Gentlemen.
- these boxes here,
and guess what strange thing
they think they're feeling.
(crowd cheering)
I am the only one that has
the answers, right here.
And, we'll reveal what's in each box.
- Okay, we're ready.
- Are you fellas ready?
- Wait, so you know what's in the box?
- She, she knows--
- Yes, I know
what's in the box.
- No!
- We do not.
And, we each have a hole.
- It is disgusting.
- Here we go.
- Let's go, alright?
- One, two, three.
- Two, three, do it.
(screaming)
- Oh my God, it's oatmeal!
- Mmm.
- It's oatmeal.
- Feels like oatmeal.
- That's oatmeal.
- Oh my God, it's disgusting.
- You are incorrect.
- Wait, wait.
- It is relish.
- I knew it was relish.
- Oh, you can see.
- I smelled it.
- Gross.
- Ayy, I just--
- Gross!
(Kelly laughs)
(Ryan mumbles)
- No, that's okay.
- I didn't even say my answer.
- Next.
- Alright, next one.
Next one, next one.
- Next one.
- So, you just put your hand
in the relish for no reason.
- For no reason.
- I didn't.
- You didn't put your hand in the relish?
- Here's towels.
- Wait, you didn't
put your hand in?
That's so unfair.
- 'Cause, everyone went in.
- You know what?
Finn is a thinker.
See this, he's like,
"I'm not putting my
hand in there."
- I double cross everyone.
Everyone went in,
and I was like "No."
- Next one, next one.
- Okay, next one.
On your mark, get set, go.
- Jello!
- Oh.
- No, it's Jello.
- You are correct!
- Ooh.
- Yes, Jello.
- Oh yeah, that feels so good.
- Doesn't feel as
gross as the relish.
- Ew dude, don't eat it.
- It's Jello.
- Ew, that's disgusting.
- It's Jello, it's Jello.
- It's like relish-Jello.
- It's relish-Jello.
- Oh, we don't have to
wipe our hands then.
- Did it taste a
- Rello.
- Little bit like relish?
Yeah, it's like Rello.
- No, like Jello.
- Jello, okay good.
- Like Rello?
- Alright, good.
- Alright, next one.
- Next one, number three.
- Just--
- A marshmallow fluff!
- Oh, it's marshmell--
Oh, it feels like a pillow!
- No, it is...
- Oh, oh, cream!
- Shaving cream?
- Shaving cream!
- Shaving cream.
- Yes!
- It smells like
shaving cream.
- You are correct!
Shaving cream!
- High-five, high-five.
- This the first (mumbles).
- High-five.
Okay.
- Get it together.
- You still have relish
on your hands.
- Noah!
- Oh my God,
this feels so nice.
- It smells so good.
- I should go, tempting.
- You guys...
- Oh.
- Smells so good.
You guys...
- Oh.
- Alright, next one.
- Try me.
(laughing)
- Aright, aright, cool.
- Alright, get in there,
get in there, get in there.
- I guess I'm--
- You know what?
- Great!
- Finn, the Canadian,
could be my favorite new player
of this game.
- Finn's Canadian.
- Why?
- Can that be his
- Finn, have you put your
- Official new name?
- Hands in anything yet?
- Yes, look at his hands.
- Okay, alright.
I thought for sure he
- No.
- Was three for three.
- Not anymore, Finn.
- I have not.
- You could not get this
- Okay, next one.
- Off your hands, can you?
- Next one.
- Feels so nice.
- Okay.
- Okay, do it.
- [Ryan] Oh, this feels great.
Worms.
- Oh, worms, gummy worms.
- Gummy, um...
It's a gummy worm, right?
- Yeah, they are gummy worms.
- It's gummy worms.
(muffled crosstalk)
- Yeah, I felt worms--
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're like--
- I felt worms on
this show before.
- Yeah!
- I just wanna say one thing.
(stammers) Ryan is cheating.
- [Ryan] So, they feel like real worms.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- Ryan?
- Ryan, you're not allowed
to pull it out of the thing.
- Ryan!
- Oh that's...
Now you tell me.
- Just telling you.
Those are the rules.
- I didn't hear
that in the rules.
You can't pull it outta the thing.
- This is for all the marbles.
- Let's get to the next box.
I won't pull it out of
this thing.
- This is for
all the marbles.
- All I got from this was--
- High-five, high-five,
high-fave, partner.
(laughing)
- Oh!
- Alright, next one.
- Real consequence--
- Wait, Finn, what is it?
All you got from this is what?
- Clean hands.
- And, a clean shave.
- See that.
- Yeah.
- Okay, guys.
- This is the final box.
- This is the final one,
and this one is...
- Oh yeah.
- You earn your--
- No!
- Come on.
- What is it?
- Do it.
- Oh my God.
- I don't know.
What do you think it is?
- Stop.
- Wait, Noah, no. Wait, not yet.
- Oh, I thought we were
going in.
- It's already in.
It's already in (gasps).
- What do you think it is?
- Nope.
- It feels like an intestine.
- I don't even know what that is.
- Spaghetti?
- I don't wanna know
what that is.
- EW.
Oh my gosh, meatballs.
- It's not spaghetti.
- Meatballs!
Not meatballs.
- Is it chicken?
- Ground meat?
- Is it manure?
- Ground beef?
- It's not manure.
- Is it something--
- Oh!
- It's a liver?
- I feel it!
- Nope.
- It's ground beef.
- I'm squeezing it.
- It's not ground beef.
- [Ryan] Alright, we're out of
guesses.
- You ready?
- Steak?
- Reveal.
- It's not snake.
- Steak!
- It is, oh.
No, it's wet hotdog buns.
- Oh.
- Ew!
(audience laughing and scoffing)
- [Kelly] You're welcome, everybody.
(audience applauding and cheering)
- You guys are good sports.
High-five, high-five,
high-five, high-five.
- No!
(laughing)
Gentlemen...
- I want the shaving cream.
- Gentlemen, I'm proud--
(Ryan shouts)
(stammers) I'm proud to present you
with these incredible trophies.
- Each of you are winners.
Ah (laughs)!
- Oh, wow.
- You're all--
- Thanks, guys.
Congratulations on season
three.
- You're all winners.
- Are we all winners?
- I didn't guess any of 'em.
- Hey, Ryan?
Guess what?
- Oh, I get one too?
- You win a prize too.
- That's right.
- Alright, alright.
- No one goes home empty-handed.
- Hey, Finn Wolfhard, Noah Schnapp,
Caleb McLaughlin, and Gaten Matarazzo,
the stars of "Stranger Things."
- Well done guys, well done.
We'll be right back!
(audience applauding and cheering)
- [Announcer] Tomorrow
on Live, Ricky Gervais.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Today,
people across the nation
are experiencing the benefits of
joining PENFED Credit Union.
With the PENFED car buying service,
they're finding the right
car at a better price.
And, everyone is welcome to apply.
Join today at PENFED.org.
- [Narrator] You left
your family alone tonight,
but you're not worried about what
you'll find when you come home.
You're thinking about how great it is
to have actual adult conversations,
with actual adults.
You're thinking about how you've
only lived in the
neighborhood a few weeks,
but it's already starting
to feel like home.
(quiet murmurs)
You're not worried about
what's going on at home.
Well, maybe just a little.
(whimsical music)
Stay close to the moments that matter.
COX Homelife takes care of the rest.
- My stylish Caleb sofa and loveseat have
super comfy Bob-O-Pedic memory foam,
and four matching throw pillows.
And, with Bob's discount,
you get both pieces for just $799.
- $799, are you joking?
- Do I look like I'm joking?
- You're a two-foot-tall
smiling spokes-puppet.
Yes, you look like you're joking.
- I'm serious.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
- Cool.
- [Group] Get Bob's discount!
- [Narrator] Only at
Bob's Discount Furniture.
- [Narrator] Ballston Quarter.
Enjoy indoor and outdoor shopping.
Dining and entertainment.
Right off the Metro.
Check out Quarter Market.
With 10 eateries from
the region's top chefs.
With more to come.
Ballston Quarter,
Arlington's top destination
for food and fun.
- I'm Kidd O'shea.
Check out Cooking With
Kidd, every Tuesday,
as the area's top chef's and foodie's
join me in the kitchen.
See what we're cooking
on ABC7 News, at 4:00.
- [Narrator] Cooking With Kidd is brought
to you by Ballston Quarter and Cookology.
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm Dan, from MarketPro Homebuyers,
and we wanna buy your home.
Don't make repairs, don't pay commissions,
and don't wait another day.
We'll get you the cash you need.
No agent fees, no closing costs.
We'll even help you
pack and move for free.
For a no-obligation
offer, call 301-750-SELL.
That's 301-750-7355.
Or visit marketprohomebuyers.com.
We buy houses as is, on your schedule.
Call today.
- [Narrator] With the
PENFED car buying service,
from PENFED Credit Union,
you can get rates as low as
2.49% APR on used vehicles.
And, everyone is welcome to apply.
Visit PENFED.org.
♪ PENFED's got great rates for everyone ♪
(food sizzling)
- [Narrator] If your grillin's got game,
and you have a dish that
inspires high-praise,
then you'd be perfect for our
Grillin'Spiration Summer Cookoff.
Tell us about your dish,
and you might have a chance to come here
to inspire everyone at
home to get cookin'!
Send us your recipe,
and a short video,
telling us all about what
makes your dish so popular.
And, let's add a little
Grillin'Spiration to the Summer.
Go to KELLYandRYAN.com to find out
more details on how to enter.
♪ You smile ♪
♪ Baby we're only here ♪
♪ Oh, for a little while ♪
(audience applauding and cheering)
- O.A.R, right there.
- It's amazing.
- Good to see
those guys.
- I love having
O.A.R here as our house band.
It's amazing.
- So good.
- Thank you, guys.
- Thank you, very much.
- Fourth of July games continue.
For this challenge,
we've each partnered
with an audience member.
My teammate is Sara Hollis,
from Edmond, Oklahoma.
Good to meet you.
- My winning partner
is Victoria Stultsman,
from Elsie, Michigan.
And, in this game,
what do we have?
60 seconds.
- 60 seconds, yeah.
- To find red and blue necklaces.
Okay?
- Blue for us, red for you.
- Yes, red for us.
We have to put them on our necks.
Right?
- Kay, correct.
- We cannot, we're not allowed to sabotage
the other team by throwing their colors
out of the--
- Did you hear that?
You're not allowed to
sabotage the other team.
- Did you hear it?
You're not allowed to
sabotage the other team.
- Okay, fine.
Alright, here we go, Sarah.
- You know what
he's trying to do?
He's trying to feel
around on the ground.
- Uh-huh.
(laughing)
I know where they are.
- I'm all over it.
- Okay.
Now--
- Now, the winner.
- Okay, so Elsie and I,
are looking for the red necklaces.
Ryan and Sara are looking
for the blue ones.
Once we put them on our necks,
we're gonna find out who wins.
Right?
- That's right.
- And, whoever wins,
wins 10 million dollars.
(audience hollering)
- The team with the
most combined necklaces,
wins a 500 dollar gift
card from Barnes & Noble.
- Which is the same thing
as 10 million dollars.
- Ready?
- Yes.
- Set.
Go.
(ball pit rumbling)
(playful music)
(Ryan mumbles)
(audience hollering and cheering)
- Oh.
- [Kelly] Monster!
You are (laughs).
(Ryan mumbles)
You're a monster.
(Kelly and Ryan laughing)
(Ryan mumbles)
Crazy.
(audience cheering)
(Kelly laughs)
(ball pit rumbling)
(audience cheering)
- [Ryan] Oh my God.
I can't find--
(audience cheering)
(ball pit rumbling)
(lady screams)
(Ryan sighs)
- [Audience] Five, four,
three, two, one (cheers).
(bell dinging)
- You know what?
I'm not gonna lie, that got violent.
(laughing)
- [Ryan] I got all the red ones.
- Woo! Woo!
(Ryan sighs)
- [Gelman] Alright, everyone count
everything they have
- Okay, but we need (mumbles).
- Oh, hey, well.
- Get the count.
- [Ryan] Alright, count 'em up, Sara.
How many do you have?
- Okay.
- One.
- Alright.
- Two.
- This was much
easier as a kid.
- Three.
- Kay.
- Okay.
- This one doesn't count?
- Four.
- Oh, gosh.
(Gelman mumbles)
- That's disqualified.
- The red one counts,
but the blue ones doesn't.
- Five.
- Okay, five.
- Six.
- Seven.
- Eight.
- Nine.
- Ten.
- Eleven!
- Eleven, okay.
- Okay.
- 11 blues.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
- Seven, eight, nine,
Ten, eleven, twelve.
- Yeah!
- Ryan!
(audience applauding and cheering)
(laughing)
- I got none.
- How?
- Sorry, sorry.
- You're fine (laughs).
- I didn't get one.
- And guys, I'm not gonna lie.
Ryan and I full-on punched
each other (mumbles).
(laughing)
(Ryan stammers)
- Alright Sara,
thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Thanks for being here.
- It was hair removal.
- There was all kinds of going on.
We'll be right back,
with cornhole, after the break.
(audience applauding and cheering)
- Woo-hoo!
- Oh my gosh.
♪ Just wanna make you laugh ♪
♪ Just wanna see that smile ♪
- [Announcer] Monday, on Live,
Wrestler, turned actor, Dave Bautista.
♪ Oh, for a little while ♪
♪ I just wanna hold you 'til ♪
♪ We fall asleep ♪
♪ I want love ♪
♪ I want us ♪
- [Announcer] Next Live, Ricky Gervais.
- You look great.
Are you on a routine right now?
- Yeah, I eat and drink
too much every night.
(laughing)
- [Announcer] Plus, Goo Goo Dolls perform.
And, girls love Pauly D..
- Listen, I watch the Jersey Shore.
I know.
- Yeah.
- [Narrator] I'm 52.
But, in my mind, I'm still 25.
That's why I take Osteo Bi-Flex.
To keep me moving the way I was made to.
It nourishes and strengthens
my joints for the long-term.
- [Narrator] Osteo Bi-Flex,
now in triple strength plus Magnesium.
- Can you love wearing powerful sunscreen?
Yes.
- [Narrator] Neutrogena Ultra Sheer.
Unbeatable protection helps
prevent early skin aging
and skin cancer, with a clean feel.
- The best for your skin.
- [Narrator] Ultra Sheer, Neutrogena.
♪ Ooh yeah ♪
(crowd chatter)
♪ Alright ♪
(crowd cheering)
♪ Here we go, now ♪
♪ Give a little bit of my love to you ♪
- [Narrator] Find great summer trends
at Macy's July fourth sale.
And, get an extra 20 percent
off with your coupon or Macy's card.
Plus, Star rewards members
can ear toward Star money,
and use it with no merchandise exclusions.
Now, at Macy's.
- [Narrator] People
aren't talking about how
Giant carries local
dry-aged steaks and burgers.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Mmm.
Looks delicious.
At Giant, we believe in local.
Because, we offer fresh food you love,
from the place you call home.
(uplifting music)
- [Narrator] There are
as many American dreams
as there are Americans.
And PENFED Credit Union is their champion.
Whether our members are dreaming
of reunions or road trips.
A daily homecoming.
Or the vacation of a lifetime.
We support them.
So, dream your American dream.
We'll provide the products,
people, and great rates,
to help make it come true.
Everyone is eligible to apply.
See how easy it is at PENFED.org.
(uplifting music)
- [Narrator] People
aren't talking about how
Giant's fresh local seafood
is 100 percent sustainable.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
May I?
At Giant, we believe in local.
Because, we offer fresh food you love,
from the place you call home.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
- Well, well, well.
We've recovered from that,
and we're back.
- How do you feel?
Are you okay?
- I'm sore.
I'm bruised.
- Aw.
- I was strangled.
(audience laughing)
- I mean, you have lots
of illegal moves there.
I watched the tape in the break.
- The only move that I heard,
that was illegal,
was taking your blue necklaces,
and throwing them outside the ball pit.
- That's...
(audience laughing)
That's right, cheater.
- That's right.
It wouldn't be a Fourth of July party
without a fun game of cornhole.
- Alright.
- Mhm.
(audience applauding and cheering)
- But--
- Today...
The highest ranked
players will be competing
against each other at the
National Cornhole Championship.
- We have the top male,
and top female competitors,
from the American Cornhole
League here today.
Please welcome Cody Henderson,
and Stacia Pugh.
- Yeah!
(upbeat music)
(applauding and cheering)
- [Kelly] Yeah!
- How are you?
- I'm good.
How are you?
- Hi, Cody.
I'm Kelly.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi, Stacia, I'm Kelly.
Nice to meet you.
- How are you?
Good to see you.
Come on...
Come over here.
There you go.
Okay, so--
- Cody, you are 27 years old.
How did you get into
competitive corn-holing?
- I got in, in high school.
It was just a game.
I liked to have fun.
I found the professional circuit,
and for the last eight years,
I've been playing competitively.
Traveling around the country.
It's been quite the experience.
- [Ryan] And Stacia, how about for you?
- For me, I've been
playing about 10 years.
Kinda started in the
front yard, with my dad.
You know, at family events.
Just realized I liked the game,
and played more, and more (laughs).
- Played more, and more.
Okay, is there something we should know?
We're not very good
corn-holers.
- Holers.
(laughing)
- We found out, recently,
- We did.
- Last Fourth of July.
- Embarrassingly, we did.
- Is there a technique?
Is there something we should know.
Like, is there a twist?
- A wrist.
A release.
- A thing?
- There is.
- Okay.
- I mean...
You know, when it comes to cornhole,
if you can throw a flat bag,
then you'll beat 90% of people.
- Alright.
- You know.
Right away.
- So, the bag should be flat?
- Yes.
- Okay, got it.
- Wait, I don't know if know (stammers).
Okay, like this?
- Flat bag.
- And, do you go like this?
- Yes.
- Well, spin.
Like, a pizza.
- Like a pizza.
- See, we're getting
more tips.
- Alright.
Let's play.
- Alright, let's play.
(audience applauding and cheering)
- Girls, versus boys.
- Yeah.
- Okay, girls versus boys.
You ready to lose again?
- Girls verse boys.
- Ugh, yes.
- Okay.
- Come on.
Let's go down here.
- Me, and you?
(applause and cheering)
- [Stacia] So, you go
over there on that side.
- [Kelly] Now, am I allowed to block the--
- [Cody] No, you can't do any of that.
- Okay.
- Can I hit Ryan
for no reason?
- Yes.
- Okay.
(playful music)
(thud)
Oh my gosh.
- Yeah, nice flat spin.
- Good spin, like a pizza.
- Yes.
Walk it right up the board.
♪ Crowd, when the beat go down ♪
(thud)
- [Kelly] Woo-hoo!
(applause and cheering)
(thud)
- Oh!
- Okay.
So, one got knocked in.
What does that mean?
Does that count?
- It means we got a big deal.
Yeah, we're tied up there.
- Okay.
- That's pretty close.
- [Stacia] We call that a replacement bag.
- [Kelly] A replacement bag?
- Replacement bag.
- Okay, got it.
(bag rustling)
(upbeat music)
♪ Crowd, when the beat go down ♪
(thud)
- Ugh.
- Okay.
Now, you knocked in his.
So, we get that point?
- No.
♪ When the beat go down ♪
(thud)
- [Ryan] Ugh.
So close.
(upbeat music)
(thud)
- Ugh.
- Okay.
- Now what?
- [Cody] Okay, now you're
gonna throw 'em back.
- We throw them back.
- Alright, everyone have the,
we calculated this?
- [Cody] Yeah, so there's
three points there.
- But, what about these that are so close?
Do we get anything for that?
- No.
- Okay.
- No, so it would be
one on the board,
three in the hole,
that round was an eight on five,
we get three.
- Okay.
- [Cody] So, we have a three point lead.
- You go first, right?
Right, Ry?
- You'll be on that side.
- Onto this side.
- Right there.
- You're across from me.
- Okay, got it (laughs).
- [Cody] Okay Ryan, (mumbles).
- [Kelly] And, don't let any
of this make you nervous.
Don't let this unnerve you.
- I don't think I
can do the pizza spin.
- You can totally do the pizza.
You love pizza.
- I do.
But, I can't do the toss.
- Just try it.
Toss it.
Toss it, Ryan.
- [Man] Come on, Ryan.
(cheering)
(thud)
- Ooh.
- Oh.
(laughing)
- [Kelly] Alright, Kelly.
You learned a lot.
- Alright, Kelly.
- You learned a lot
- Woo!
- Okay.
Don't...
Don't give me protective arm.
(upbeat music)
♪ Beat go down ♪
(thud)
- Oh.
- How--
- Almost fell in the pool.
- How far over the plain
is Ryan allowed to step?
Just curious.
- Just, not in the water.
- [Cody] You can step up to the board.
- Up to the board.
- Up to the very
front of the board.
(upbeat music)
(scoffs)
- Ooh, nice try.
- Okay.
Inchin' on up there.
- We're getting there.
We're getting there.
(audience chattering)
(upbeat music)
- Oh!
- Closer, closer.
- Love you, Kelly!
- Kelly!
(laughing)
- [Kelly] Ooh, Ryan!
That was...
It was almost good.
- Almost, but not good enough.
- It was almost good.
- Story of my life.
- Come on, Kelly.
- It's harder than it looks.
- For the win.
- Oh!
(laughing)
(audience applauding and cheering)
- Thanks for (mumbles)
- Nice to meet you.
- Sorry, sorry.
I apologize.
I let you down.
- You can see the
National Cornhole Championship today.
1:00 p.m., on ESPN.
Cody, Stacia, thank you so much.
- And, coming up next--
- O.A.R performs next.
- Yes.
Stick around.
Sorry about that.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
- [Announcer] Tomorrow, on Live,
reality star, DJ Pauly D.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
♪ Hey, come on ♪
♪ Tick, tick ♪
♪ Tick, tick, tick ♪
♪ Keeping it fresh ♪
♪ Doing it right ♪
- [Narrator] SC Johnson.
(upbeat music)
♪ Don't give it up ♪
♪ 'Cause there's nothing
like this feeling, baby ♪
♪ Now that I found love ♪
♪ Now that I found you ♪
- [Narrator] When someone's on your side,
you feel empowered.
That's why seven on your side is here,
to help you fight back
when you're taken advantage of.
And, to give you information to make
the right decisions for your family.
ABC7 News, on your side.
- [Narrator] Storm Watch 7.
- Knowing where the threat is,
and knowing when it will impact you.
- Knowing Storm Watch
7 is always on alert.
Always with you.
- That makes all the difference.
- [Narrator] Storm Watch 7, seven strong,
and always on your side.
- [Narrator] Across the nation,
people are joining PENFED Credit Union,
and getting more from their mortgages.
We offer low rates, and superior service,
to give our members the power
to purchase their perfect home.
And, everyone is welcome to apply.
Visit PENFED.org.
(Honda chime)
- [Narrator] Get ready for clearance.
It's the Honda fourth of July sales event.
Accords on a clearance.
Civics on clearance.
CR-Vs and HR-Vs on clearance.
Even the third-row Pilot is on clearance.
With features on clearance,
safety on clearance,
and selection on clearance.
Like a new Civic for just $189 a month.
Or, get a new CR-V for just $259 a month.
Don't miss the Honda
fourth of July sales event.
Did we mention is was clearance?
Going on now, at your local Honda dealer.
- With COX, you get everything you
wanna watch in one place,
using the voice remote.
- Show me action.
- Even a ninny like me can figure it out.
With streaming apps,
you miss live events,
and waste time searching for shows.
- Not this one. That one?
- [Narrator] It's clear that
COX is the better choice.
Just like it's clear
that the teleprompter guy
thinks I'm a boo-boo-head
who steals parking spots.
(adventurous music)
- [Narrator] Get live TV, great apps,
and On Demand, from COX.
Starting at $79.99 a month.
- [Narrator] This is Will,
preparing for takeoff.
(phone buzzing)
And, this is a loving
reminder from his wife.
(upbeat music)
- [Woman] Tray table.
- [Narrator] This is Will finally
depositing that expense check.
- [Woman] Seat belts.
(upbeat music)
(camera shutter clicks)
(phone buzzing)
- [Narrator] Oh, and
this is Will paying his
brother-in-law back with Zelle,
for their annual camping trip.
- [Woman] Seat back.
(upbeat music)
(sniffling)
- [Narrator] And, this
is Will finally relaxing
for the long flight.
This is your right here, right now, bank.
This is Wells Fargo.
- [Narrator] At PENFED Credit Union,
we help you get more from your mortgage.
By offering some of the lowest
rates on mortgages around.
Everyone is welcome to apply.
Visit PENFED.org.
♪ PENFED's got great rates for everyone. ♪
(audience applauding and cheering)
- Welcome back.
Alright, they've been house-banding it,
but now we're ready.
O.A.R's new album is available now.
Here they are,
with a brand new hit,
"Knocking at Your Door",
O.A.R.
(audience applauding and cheering)
♪ Oh I know ♪
♪ I've been here before ♪
♪ Alone ♪
♪ So long ♪
♪ Thousand miles to shore ♪
♪ Thought a thousand angels could fly ♪
♪ By me ♪
♪ Oh, please ♪
♪ Carry me through the night ♪
♪ Because, I got ♪
♪ Not a minute more ♪
♪ I need a miracle ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I wanna let you know ♪
♪ That you're not alone ♪
♪ So, I'm coming home ♪
♪ Who's knocking at your door ♪
♪ It's me coming back for more ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
♪ I'm not far away ♪
♪ Time is my enemy ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
♪ Be there ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ I'm moving all these mountains aside ♪
♪ Moving all these mountains ♪
♪ No one will fall ♪
♪ While you sleep through the night ♪
♪ Because, I gotta go ♪
♪ Not a minute more ♪
♪ I need a miracle ♪
♪ I wanna let you know ♪
♪ That you're not alone ♪
♪ So, I'm coming home ♪
♪ Yeah, who's knocking at your door ♪
♪ It's me coming back for more ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
♪ I'm half of the world away ♪
♪ Yeah, time is my enemy ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
♪ On my way, on my way, on my way ♪
♪ And you know I couldn't wait ♪
♪ Not a day ♪
♪ To see your face ♪
♪ Baby, now I'm on my way ♪
♪ On my way, on my way ♪
♪ You know, believe me say ♪
♪ I'm on the way ♪
♪ I'm on my way ♪
♪ Yeah, who's knocking at your door ♪
♪ It's me coming back for more ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
♪ I'm half of the world away ♪
♪ Time is my enemy ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
♪ Be there ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
♪ On my way, on my way, on my way ♪
(audience applauding and cheering)
(whistling)
- Come on.
- O.A.R!
- Thank you.
- That was amazing.
- Good to see you guys again.
Good to see you, boys.
- Hi.
- So good to see you.
- Great to see you.
- Thank you, Ryan.
As always, thank you.
- Thanks guys.
Thank you for house-banding as well,
for this Fourth of July.
- It was our pleasure.
- I gotta tell you,
you really like,
brought the holiday spirit.
It was great.
- I think you brought,
you brought the holiday spirit.
- Well, we do try.
- It's a team effort.
- We try.
- Fantastic.
- O.A.R's new album,
it is out now.
Go pick it up.
- Yeah, pick it up.
- [Ryan] These guys are the best.
We'll be right back.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] If you'd like to know more
about anything you see on Live,
just log onto our website,
at kellyandryan.com.
(applause and cheering)
- [Narrator] Far from ordinary.
And now, far closer
than you ever imagined.
Call 1-800-Sandals.
- I would get muscle cramps
several times a week, for decades.
Using Theraworx Relief,
the cramps are gone.
- [Narrator] Get Theraworx Relief, today.
In stores everywhere.
- [Narrator] America's best-selling
windows, $279, installed.
- Window World.
Highest in satisfaction,
and America's best warranty.
Even glass breaking.
(glass shattering)
- [Narrator] $279, installed.
- Simply the best, for less.
- [Narrator] Do you have
trouble falling asleep?
Do you toss or turn all night,
or wake up with a sore
neck, or a headache?
Then it's time you discovered MyPillow.
- Hello, I'm Mike Lindell,
inventor of MyPillow.
Just like you, I had problems sleeping.
I tried every pillow out there,
and nothing worked.
15 years ago,
I invented MyPillow.
It took me two years to develop,
because I wanted to have everything
you would ever want in a pillow.
I made sure that you could
adjust my patented fill,
so you could have the exact
support you need as an individual.
Regardless of your sleep position.
I also wanted a pillow that would last.
So, I made MyPillow machine
washable, and dryable.
I back MyPillow with a 10 year warranty,
and a 60 day money-back guarantee.
Not only that,
I do all my own manufacturing,
in my home state of Minnesota.
Take advantage of my 2-pack special.
Use the promo code,
and get two MyPillow's for $69.98.
That's only $34.99 a pillow.
Call, or go online now.
- [Narrator] Other pillows go flat.
Causing you to fold them over,
or use your arm for support.
Which can cause pain.
Hard foam pillows can
raise your head too high,
and heat up during the night.
Making you very uncomfortable.
But, the revolutionary
MyPillow has patented fill
that won't go flat,
and helps keep your neck
supported, and aligned,
to your exact individual need.
MyPillow helps you get,
and stay in deep sleep,
all night long.
- Before MyPillow,
sleeping was a nightmare.
First night I got it,
slept like a baby.
Just was out, completely out.
- I sleep better.
I wake up, I feel
refreshed, I feel healthy.
- MyPillow helps me get
a good nights sleep,
so I can do my job in the morning.
- I personally guarantee
that MyPillow will be the
most comfortable pillow you'll ever own.
And, I wanna thank each
and every one of you,
for your support.
- [Narrator] Call, or go to mypillow.com,
to take advantage of
Mike's 2-pack special.
Use the promo code,
and Mike will send you
two MyPillow premiums,
for just $69.98.
That's only $34.99 a pillow.
This offer is not available in stores.
So, don't delay.
Call, or go online now.
♪ For the best night's sleep ♪
♪ In the whole-wide world ♪
♪ Visit MyPillow.com ♪
- [Narrator] America's
best-selling windows,
$279, installed.
- Window World.
Highest in satisfaction,
and America's best warranty.
Even glass breaks.
(glass shattering)
- [Narrator] $279, installed.
- Simply the best, for less.
- [Narrator] Closed captioning
sponsored, in part, by...
(upbeat music)
(sighs)
- [Man] What the, what?
Okay, wipe.
Pretty-please do your thing.
Nice.
(triumphant music)
Nailed it.
(baby coo's)
- [Narrator] Huggies Natural Care Wipes,
gentle like a hug.
Hug on.
- [Narrator] Just when you
thought you were done painting,
you discover paint bleed under your tape.
Not with FrogTape.
FrogTape is the only painters tape
treated with patented
paint-block technology.
Get professional results with FrogTape.
No messy lines.
No paint bleed.
For sharp lines,
every time,
Frog it.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
- One more time, O.A.R,
ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you, guys,
- O.A.R!
- For being here.
- Woo!
- So...
- You know what?
(ball pit rumbling)
I'm not gonna lie,
I think our barbecue was
more fun than your barbecue.
Woo!
(laughing)
- US of Yay!
Tomorrow, Ricky Gervais
is here.
- And, DJ Pauly D. is here
- Have a great holiday.
- Woo!
♪ Red, red, wine ♪
♪ Goes to my head ♪
- Are you looking for a
hassle-free, simple way,
to sell your home, as is?
We buy houses directly.
There's no middle-men.
No commissions.
Give us a call, today.
House Buyers of America.
Real-estate made real easy.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] This Price
Busters Furniture's huge
Fourth of July sale.
With huge savings, store wide,
and low, low payments.
Seven piece living room,
just $27 payments, with zero down.
Save now, get it now, and pay later,
with no money down, period.
Plus, free delivery.
Price Busters Furniture.
Get there now.
- [Narrator] People
aren't talking about how
Giant's fresh Chesapeake Bay
seafood is 100% sustainable.
They're not talking about
how our local products
are sourced from over
40 family-owned farms.
Or, how we carry local
dry-aged steaks and burgers.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Mmm.
Looks delicious.
At Giant, we believe in local.
Because, it's about offering
fresh food you love,
from the place you call home.
The little things are giant.
- With so many people trying
to buy houses these days,
reputation matters.
♪ Express Home Buyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
- [Narrator] Live,
Fourth of July coverage.
All day, on ABC7.
- Are you looking for a
hassle-free, simple way,
to sell your home, as is?
We buy houses directly.
There's no middle-men.
No commissions.
Give us a call, today.
House Buyers of America.
Real-estate made real easy.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] ABC7 News, at 6:00.
Followed by World News
Tonight, weeknights.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
- [Announcer] Today, on Rachael Ray...
- Yay!