- There you go.
I think the entire country
is rooting for those women.
We know that the White House
just announced this hour,
they're sending a delegation
over to the game in France,
led by the Deputy Commerce
Secretary and others.
It is gonna be a big one.
Nancy Cook, Tamara Keith,
thank you for coming
on the show and thank you guys all
for watching this hour of MSNBC Live.
Craig Melvin, where are you gonna be
watching the game, my friend?
- Go team USA.
I'll be watching from the comfy confines
of my basement.
My favorite place in the world.
- Very nice, big screen.
Love it.
- Thank you Hallie.
Thank you, thank you.
Craig Melvin here, MSNBC
Headquarters, New York City.
Tanks in position.
Preparations underway
for President Trump's
big Fourth of July event.
Including those military
vehicles now on the National Mall
as new details about
how it's being paid for
are generating more fury.
Also, Hawkeye swing, 2020 candidates
making there way to Iowa for the holiday
as a new poll of voters in that state
reveals some new challenges
for some of those contenders.
Two of the Democratic
contenders will join me
live this hour, two of them.
Also, ticking time bomb.
That is how one official
in a new government
Watchdog Report describes
the horrific conditions
inside migrant detention facilities.
It includes shocking
new images from inside.
We'll get to that story in just a moment,
but we start with those
tanks and military vehicles
descending on the National Mall
for President Trump's self-produced
Fourth of July event tomorrow.
In a break from tradition,
the President has ordered
a display of American
military might in the Capital.
That plan, its meaning, and its cost
all stirring controversy.
Joining me now NBC's Monica
Alba live on the National Mall.
Ashley Parker, White House reporter
for the Washington Post.
She's an MSNBC Senior Political Analyst.
Democratic Congressman
Don Bayer is with me.
His district includes Northern Virginia,
those D.C. suburbs and
Washington Post opinion writer,
Jennifer Rubin is with me
and so is Mark Updegrove,
Presidential Historian,
also the President and CEO
of the LBJ Foundation.
Quite the esteemed panel here.
Monica, I'll start with you.
What are we seeing
there on the Mall today?
- So Craig actually if I turn here
you're gonna see two
Bradley Fighting Vehicles
and these are just some
of the military might
that's gonna be on
display tomorrow evening.
This is of course being transported
on such a large flatbed
because of how heavy they are.
The Abrams tanks, which are other tanks
that are parked nearby and
going to be on the Mall,
weigh as much as 60 tons.
So you can imagine that's something
that could damage D.C.
streets and of course
some of the President's critics
have expressed concerns about that,
but that is exactly what the
President wants on display.
He wants to do the Salute to America
and feature all of these different
military vehicles after being inspired
two years ago at the Bastille
Day celebrations in Paris
where he saw the parade with
President Emmanuel Macron
and said I would very
much like to do this.
He then thought it was gonna be actually
taking place on Veterans
Day, but that got canceled,
you may remember, and
moved to the Fourth of July
because of how expensive it is.
The Washington Post is reporting
that it's gonna be at least 2.5 million
in entrance fees redirected to account
for the event tomorrow and of course
we don't know what the cost is yet
of the other military flyovers.
The President has tweeted
that a lot of that
is going to be free because
we own the equipment,
but you have to think about the security
and other concerns, other things
that are going to kind of
put that price tag up high
and we don't know how
much that's going to cost.
Now, these tanks and military vehicles
are gonna be moved.
We don't know exactly when.
We're just steps from
the Lincoln Memorial,
but they're all going to be placed
up and down the Mall,
but we don't know exactly
how many there are gonna be and tomorrow
a lot of the excitement is around
of course the military flyovers
and then also what's expected to be
a fly over of Air Force One.
So a lot of spectacle
tomorrow evening, Craig,
but that's the scene
from here the day before.
- All right Monica Alba there.
Monica, thank you.
Ashley, your paper reporting
that the National Park Service
is diverting $2.5 million in park fees
to pay for this story.
The story adds, quote,
the diverted park fees
represent just a fraction
of the extra costs
the government faces as
a result of the event,
which will include displays
of military hardware,
flyovers by an array of jets
including Air Force One,
the deployment of tanks on the Mall
and an extended pyrotechnics show.
Is there a concern at the White House
of just the sheer optics of spending
so much money on this
extravaganza at this point?
- Well there's certainly not
concern from the President,
this is what he wants,
but you can see in that tweet he sent
that he is certainly
aware of the criticism.
That's something the White House
has been very cognizant of,
when the Post first reported,
I believe that there were gonna be
sort of a longer fireworks
display than usual
because some companies had volunteered
to help with that.
One thing that the White House really
tried to make clear was that you know
these were sort of not
quite free firework shows,
but at a reduced rate
and that the President
would sort of be foolish not to take
these companies up on the offer.
So they are aware of this criticism
and keep in mind, you
mentioned this earlier,
but the whole reason that his plans
for a Veterans Day parade were scuttled
was because the price tag,
I believe it got to about 90 million,
but it was just way too high.
There was a ton of outcry,
including from the D.C. government,
it was not logistically feasible.
So again the President
may not care necessarily,
he's clearly preceding full steam ahead,
but that tweet shows
and other conversations
we've had with the White House shows
that they are at least aware
that there is a number,
there is a lot of criticism
coming from all sides.
- Ashley, what else do we know about this
reporting on the Republican
National Committee,
they received a number of VIP tickets
that they're handing out as well?
Are they handing out tickets
to a taxpayer funded event?
- Well there is concern, there has
been a lot of fair criticism about that
for sort of politicizing, you know,
one of these rare things in
the nation that is apolitical,
a holiday that is symbolic
and about fireworks
and spending time with
families and barbecues.
They've sort of tried to argue
this is no different than sometimes
tickets are handed out for
say the Easter Egg Roll
or something else on the South Lawn,
but the other thing
that is worth mentioning
that we're hearing is there's also
a lot of kind of quiet chatter
in the President's orbit that they are
deeply worried about sort of
another Inauguration fiasco,
which of course--
- No one's gonna show up.
- Right, that the President's crowds
were not as big as his predecessors
and that yeah exactly
that no one will show up.
What happens if it rains?
What happens is if we're hearing a lot
of people in D.C., a deeply blue state,
not state, but district who are not fans
of the President are fleeing town.
So, part of that it seems is designed
to kind of ensure that at
least for the camera shot
that it looks like it is packed
and there's not these sort of splotches
of green grass where the President
wants a huge crowd behind
him, celebrating him.
- Mark, give us some perspective here.
How unusual is it to
have a military display
and for a President to speak from the Mall
in the way that he is reportedly going to
on Independence Day, unprecedented or not?
- Well like almost everything
this President does,
this is unprecedented.
This is a kind of military display
that we were used to seeing
from the Soviet Union
on Red Square, on May Day, this is not
the kind of thing that we do as a nation.
We show fireworks, we have parades,
but we don't show our military hardware
to the nation and to the world,
but I think this is a President
who very much wants to
be seen as a strong man,
not only to his own citizens,
but to citizens of the world.
So it's not surprising that Donald Trump
would want to do a display like this.
- Congressman Beyer, you represent
Virginia's eighth district,
home of the Pentagon.
You're just across the
river from Washington D.C.
What's your objection
to what the President
has planned for the Fourth?
- Melvin I have three big,
first that he's taken something
that's always been bipartisan.
I grew up in the city and my dad
would load the six kids of us,
take us down to the Mall with the blanket
and the picnic basket and now it's turned
into this major partisan thing.
I'm still encouraging our folks to go
'cause I don't want it to be divisive.
I also really object
to the militarization.
I thought the historian put it out well.
When I think of tanks and
troops walking down the middle,
I'm thinking Red Square,
North Korea, Egypt,
not the United States.
Where we're gonna spend three quarters
of a trillion dollars
next year on our military,
everyone knows we're the
most powerful military
in the world.
- You also, as I understand it,
you are calling for the
President to personally reimburse
taxpayers for any infrastructure damage
caused by military hardware
brought in for the celebration.
I think you and I both know
the President's not going to do that,
but what is your goal with that demand?
- Well he's famous for
not paying his bills.
I think he still owes
the District $53 million
un-reimbursed from the Inauguration.
It's just to make the point
that when you take these very
weighty 60 ton Abrams tanks
and put them next to the Lincoln Memorial,
who knows what it's doing to D.C. roads.
There's some concern from the Park Service
that the basements under
the Lincoln Memorial
may not be able to hold this up.
It's just in a time when the Park Service
has an 11 or 12 billion
dollar infrastructure backlog
to be redirecting funds
for his vanity show
just doesn't make any sense.
- [Craig] Congressman Beyer,
I appreciate your time, Sir,
thank you, and to be clear,
you're going to go,
you're going to be there?
- I am gonna go on the
Eastern Shore with my family,
but so no I will not be there.
- [Craig] You'll be
watching on television.
- But not out of protest,
previously planned.
- [Craig] But you're encouraging
your constituents to go.
- Yeah, only because he's
the most divisive president
we've ever had but one
of our great challenges
is that we live in a divided country
and we need to be do our best to heal
and they don't have to
listen to his speech,
but they should enjoy the fireworks.
- But why encourage them to
go if you're not going to go?
- Well if I were in town I probably would,
but my wife and kids are
already on the Eastern Shore.
- Got it, got it, Congressman, thank you.
Thank you for your time.
Jennifer, I want to call your
attention to this survey.
There's a survey of American Pride,
it's from Gallup and
according to this survey,
45% of folks who are
polled are extremely proud
to be an American, that's
the second straight year
of the sub 50% readings.
That percentage has been
weakening in recent years.
To what do you attribute the drop?
- Well, first of all, I
won't be going to the Mall
and it will be in protest.
So, good for the Congressman,
he's a better person than I.
I think people are deeply
disturbed with what this president
has been doing to our
Democratic institutions,
to the rule of law, to
separation of powers,
his disrespect for the First Amendment,
calling the press the enemy of the people.
For better or worse the
President of the United States
embodies the country to some degree.
He is both the Head of State
and the Head of Government
and when people look at Donald Trump
as their representative
on the world stage,
they are not proud of him.
They find him tacky, they find him crude,
racist, homophobic, misogynistic,
you can go down the list,
and I think that deeply worries people
and I think you see that in the
Democratic presidential race
where these people are
essentially running on a platform
to restore American values
of decency, inclusiveness,
generosity, community,
because we haven't gotten
that from this president.
He's notoriously awful on
these moments when you look
to the president to heal,
to bring us together.
He is the anti-uniter and
this is just one more display,
it's also really a
contempt for government.
This is the mother of
all Hatch Act violations.
This is using the taxpayer's
money, the taxpayer's property,
really, for his own vanity
and whether it's a legal violation or not,
it is so unseemly and I would
just add one final thing.
Seeing tanks on the
Mall has the appearance
that Washington is an occupied city.
We put tanks on the street
when there is a civil uprising,
when there is a calamity of some type.
There is not and Donald Trump doesn't get
that this is not a symbol
of pride or of American,
but that this is a deeply disturbing sign
that he is politicizing the military
and militarizing the
politics of our country.
- Mark, are we at a
point now where we can't
separate our patriotism
from the President?
- Well, I think those plunging
numbers around American pride
are totally reflective of the fact
that we're in a polarized nation.
We have a president who is leading
through division and discord.
You're seeing that
number increase slightly
among Republicans and
plunge among Democrats.
We are a very divided society,
but I worry too, Craig,
about what Ronald Reagan
warned about in his
Farewell Address in 1989,
he talked about the eradication
of the American memory
and the erosion of the American spirit,
by which he meant we're not
studying civics and history
in our schools anymore.
We're looking only at the moment right now
in American history and what
Donald Trump means to America,
not the larger American story
and I think if Americans,
more Americans were to
understand more about civics
and about American history,
they would have pride in our nation
knowing that sometimes
we go through good times
and sometimes we go through bad times,
but we are a strong and
resilient nation ultimately.
- On this eve of the Fourth of July,
that seems an appropriate spot to end it.
Thank you so much for that, Mark.
Thank you, Ashley.
Thank you, Jennifer,
and thank you, Monica.
I do appreciate your reporting.
Dangerous conditions, children
laying on top of each other,
cells packed at five times their capacity.
New images being released
as part of a government Watchdog Report
on conditions inside those
migrant detention facilities,
it's triggering more
outrage across the country
and on the campaign trail.
I'll talk about it with one of
the Democratic presidential contenders.
Washington Governor Jay Inslee
will join me on the
other side of this break.
Later in this hour another contender,
Ohio Congressman Tim
Ryan, will also join me.
He's got a warning for his party
on the issue of immigration
and what it could mean
for the presidential race.
- [Announcer] Stay tuned to get
a free pan from Granitestone.
Stuck on eggs, burnt on batter.
You can scrub and scrape,
but you can't escape the
nightmare of your sticky pans.
Introducing the Granitestone pan.
The all new durable, non-stick pan.
No butter or oil needed.
Watch, we melted down these
sticky candies in Granitestone
and it just doesn't stick!
We cooked a half a dozen eggs, bacon,
cheese, and tomato breakfast
with no butter or oil and
it just doesn't stick.
Look!
Caramels, chocolate and cheese!
Unreal for any other pan,
but not for Granitestone.
It just doesn't stick.
Granitestone will be the
last pan you'll ever need
because it's pressed from
a solid aluminum disk
for even heat conduction,
then coated three times
with our durable Granitestone finish.
Granitestone is metal utensil safe
and won't scratch and
talk about non-stick.
This salmon cooked skin side down
with no added butter or
oil just doesn't stick.
This steak is perfectly
seared just like the pros
and because Granitestone is
oven rated to 500 degrees,
we baked this upside down
pan pizza to perfection
and it just doesn't stick.
Fire flambe delicious cherries jubilee,
plus it's PFOA free and
100% dishwasher safe.
Call or go online to get
your Granitestone pan
for the special TV discount
price of just 19.99.
Granitestone is so durable it
comes with a 10 year warranty
and with every order, you're going to get
a Granitestone single serve
egg pan absolutely free.
It's the perfect size for
personalized eggs, omelets,
or frittatas that slide right out.
It makes the best bacon, egg,
and cheese sandwich quick.
Yours absolutely free.
We'll even ship your entire order free.
That's right, free shipping.
You get it all, an incredible value.
Here's how to order.
- [Announcer] To order
call 1-800-615-7903.
That's 1-800-615-7903 or order online
at BuyGranitestone.com.
That's 1-800-615-79.
♪ Limu Emu ♪
- [Announcer] and Doug.
- What do all these people
have in common, Limu?
Exactly, nothing, they're
completely different people,
that's why they need
customized car insurance
from Liberty Mutual, they'll
only pay for what they need.
Yes, and they could save a ton.
You've done it again Limu.
- [Announcer] Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty, Liberty, Liberty ♪
- Tell him we're flexible.
- Don't worry, my Dutch is okay.
- Just okay?
- M-hm.
(speaks in foreign language)
- Tell him we need this merger.
- It's happening.
- Just okay is not okay,
especially when it comes to your network.
AT&T is America's best wireless network
according to America's biggest test.
Now with 5G evolution
the first step to 5G.
More for your thing, that's our thing.
- [Announcer] Call now.
- Isn't this a situation
of hate the game not the player?
This is a power play.
This is a strategic move from her, right?
- Why is this potentially such a big deal?
- We have more breaking news.
Why wouldn't we?
It's Tuesday in Washington.
- The wall is the sticking
point, not border security.
- Although the promise was
a wall paid for by Mexico.
- I can not wait to
keep talking about 2020.
I gotta tell you, I
think it's fascinating.
- Your entire business is profiting
off of other people's information
then your job is to keep
that information safe.
(tense music)
- A disturbing new report from the office
of the Inspector General
highlights the conditions
migrants are facing at
the southern border.
It includes images of people
at a Rio Grande Valley Detention Center
crammed into holding cells,
sleeping on concrete floors.
One senior manager at that
facility calls the situation
a, quote, ticking time bomb.
Officials found adults and children living
with limited access to showers
and according to that report, quote,
at one facility, some
single adults were held
in standing room only conditions
for a week and at another,
some single adults were held
for more than a month
in overcrowded cells.
Joining me now, live
from Seattle, Washington,
Governor and Democratic
presidential candidate Jay Inslee.
Governor, thank you for your time.
- You bet.
- As president, what would you do
about these detention facilities?
How would they change in
an Inslee Administration?
- Well, we would stop the gross inhumanity
and you need to understand
the depth of depravity of Donald Trump.
These conditions are an
intentional action by him.
He has made it very clear
that he wants to make people afraid
and he likes these inhumane conditions
because it is part of his intention
to fan the flame of
discord around immigration
and instead of uniting us to
find a comprehensive solution,
instead of trying to
address the root causes
of this immigration problem to keep people
where they live and not
force them to come north,
he has decided to utilize
inhumane conditions
as a tool of his gross cruelty.
We need to understand how
deep this depravity is.
So we need to have both
additional capacity for people,
but we need to go back,
what we've done for 50 years,
as a judge ordered yesterday in Seattle,
to allow people to be released on bond
in the appropriate circumstances,
where as much as 80 or 90% of people
do return for their immigration hearings.
We've done that for 50 years in America.
He has departed from American tradition.
We need to go back to that.
- Last night fellow Democratic candidate,
former Housing Secretary Julian Castro,
he appeared on Rachel Maddow
and he laid out his immigration plan.
Take a listen.
- I'm gonna offer a
completely different vision
of what we should do on immigration
to make sure that we have
an immigration system
that's fixed, that works
with border security,
but that never treats
people like this again.
I believe one centerpiece of
that is repealing Section 13-25
of the Immigration Nationality Act,
so that not only this
president but future presidents
can't ever use that law
to incarcerate parents
and then separate them
from their little children.
- Do you agree with Castro's
stance that crossing
the border illegally
should be criminalized?
- We should not use criminal statutes
to separate children from
their parents, period,
and if that's being used for that purpose
it should not be used for that
purpose and is not required.
Look we have lots of
civil systems to be able
to prevent illegal entry
into the United States
and to use Donald Trump's separation
of children from parents, which
he has done intentionally,
should not be allowed
through criminal statutes
in the United States and I want to repeat,
look, for 50 years we've had a system
of being able to allow people
to have a hearing on asylum
without separating children
from their parents,
we need to restore that
basic American value.
- I want to highlight something
from the new Washington
Post ABC News poll.
It was taken since last week's NBC debate,
29% of Democratic voters say healthcare
is one of the most important issues
they're going to be voting
on, topped the list in fact.
You have relied heavily on climate change.
You've drilled down on climate change.
What do you offer voters who are looking
for someone to tackle our
nation's healthcare issues?
- Well, we have done so much
in our state successfully,
not just in addressing the climate crisis.
We've adopted the very
first public health option
in the United States.
We're proud of that.
I'm the first governor to actually
work with our community
to pass those bills,
but we've done so much on our other issues
to help families health,
health is not just
the healthcare system, you
gotta have a family wage.
That's why I'm proud to say we've adopted
while I'm governor the
highest minimum wage
in the United States.
You have to be able to
take care of your family
when they're sick and that's why we have
the most robust, comprehensive
family medical leave
in the United States.
You have to have a decent wage in general
that's why I'm proud of we've won
the highest educator compensation increase
for our teachers and educators
in the United States.
We have wrap around services of being able
to build a middle class, that's
how you really have health,
but I do want to come back to this issue.
Look this is a health issue
of this climate crisis
it's increasing Lyme disease,
it's respiratory distress,
it's an epidemic of asthma,
it's your town burning down
where 80 plus people
have died in forest fires
in California last year.
The climate crisis is a health issue
and I am offering a unique emphasis on it.
I am the candidate and
so far the only candidate
who said this will be
the number one priority
of the United States.
This is a health issue, it
is a national security issue,
it is an economic issue
all rolled into one.
- [Craig] It is your central message.
- You bet.
- The latest CNN poll, let's
talk about another poll,
it shows your movement
over the last four months,
it shows in March, April, and June
you were registering at about 1%.
In the most recent poll,
you're now at an asterisk.
Is it that message or is
it perhaps the messenger?
- Well listen we started at about one,
were about one now in the last polls.
We're where Clinton and
Carter were when they started.
We are still introducing
ourselves to the American people,
less than a third of the people
could pick me out of a line up.
This is a start, we've had some confidence
since the last debate we
had a surge of support
with the largest number
of donors in 24 hours
since I started, we had the largest number
of new donors and we encourage folks
to go to jayinslee.com if they want
to see the climate crisis
to remain a central focus in our debate.
- You're talking numbers here.
You've got some
fundraising numbers for us?
- Yeah, they're going up.
I don't have a total number for you.
I haven't totaled them for the quarter,
but we did have the best
day, the best two days
that we've had during the campaign
after the last debate and I think it is
because people want to see
the climate crisis front and center.
- Yesterday, Senator
Sanders put out his numbers,
he was around 24 million.
The day before that Mayor
Pete put out his numbers,
he was around 24 million.
Are you around 24 million?
- No, we won't be in that same league
because we're still introducing ourselves
and we're making sure
that the climate crisis
and by the way I was honored the other day
someone evaluated our
respective climate plans
and ours was held to be the number one.
I'm proud of that and I think
that is what is necessary for our nation
to address something that is burning down
our towns and flooding our fields
and if people want to see that
they can go to jayinslee.com.
- Governor Inslee, thank you.
Thanks for your time, Sir.
- You bet.
- Top tier shuffle, how the latest
post NBC News debate poll shaking up
some of the top contenders as Joe Biden
remains at the top spot though.
We're gonna go live to
Iowa where an onslaught
of candidates are hitting
the ground for holiday.
We'll catch up with our road warriors
in the Hawkeye State.
This is a live look at Des Moines.
(light music)
(tense music)
- This is political insanity.
- [Announcer] When you
need a passionate start
to the morning.
- Name one of the Democratic contenders.
Name one that you are
positive can beat Trump.
- [Announcer] You need your Morning Joe,
weekdays at 6:00 on MSNBC.
(light music)
- [Announcer] Corey is living
with metastatic breast cancer
which is breast cancer that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking Ibrance
with an aromatase inhibitor
which is for postmenopausal women
or for men with HR+ HER2-
metastatic breast cancer
as the first hormonal-based therapy.
Ibrance plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease
progression versus letrozole.
Patients taking Ibrance can develop
low white blood cell counts,
which may cause a serious
infections that can lead to death.
Before taking Ibrance tell your doctor
if you have fever, chills,
or other signs of infection,
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects
include low red blood cell
and low platelet counts, infections,
tiredness, nausea, sore
mouth, abnormalities
in liver blood tests, diarrhea,
hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash, and loss of appetite.
Corey calls it her new normal
because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about Ibrance.
The number one prescribed, FDA approved
oral combination treatment
for HR+ HER2- MBC.
- No, wrong move, old
fashioned bandages get dirty,
they can let in water and germs.
Look, it's falling off.
New-Skin is the flexible liquid bandage
that seals out the bad stuff.
There's a spray too.
- [Announcer] New-Skin,
rethink how you heal.
♪ Na na na na ♪
♪ Hey hey hey, goodbye ♪
- [Announcer] The world's
first six function
multi-pro tailgate.
Available only on the next
generation GMC Sierra.
Get 20% below MSRP on next generation
2019 GMC double cab
and SLE crew cab models
with a standard tailgate.
- [Narrator] This is
the story of John Smith.
Not this John Smith or this John Smith
or any of the other
hundreds of John Smiths
that are Humana Medicare
Advantage members.
No, it's this John Smith who we paired
with a Humana team member to help address
his own specific health needs.
At Humana we take a personal approach
to your health to provide care
that's just as unique as you are.
No matter what your name is.
- Paid Spokesperson.
- Attention.
This is a legal alert for anyone
who has used Roundup weed killer
and been diagnosed with
non-hodgkin's lymphoma.
If you used Roundup weed killer
and have been diagnosed
with non-hodgkin's lymphonma
you may be entitled to
significant compensation.
A multi-million dollar verdict
was recently awarded to a man
whose non-hodgkin's lymphoma was linked
to Roundup weed killer.
If you used Roundup weed killer
and were diagnosed with
non-hodgkin's lymphoma
you may be entitled to
significant compensation.
Call now.
♪ Limu Emu ♪
- [Announcer] And Doug.
- What do all these people
have in common Limu?
Exactly, nothing.
They're completely different people,
that's why they need
customized car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay for what they need.
Yes, and they could save a ton.
You've done it again, Limu.
- [Announcer] Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty, Liberty, Liberty ♪
- [Announcer] Recruiter.com/star.
- All right now, a lot of the
2020 Democratic presidential candidates
are swarming Iowa preparing
for a long holiday weekend.
There's a look at 'em there.
A new poll from the Washington Post
and ABC News sheds some light on how
they are stacking up at
this early point in the race
and the latest poll since
the NBC News debate,
Joe Biden's lead over
his closest competitors
shrank to just six points.
Bernie Sanders holding on to
that second spot in the poll.
Elizabeth Warren holding steady at 11%.
The biggest jump, Senator
Kamala Harris also at 11%,
but this poll is unique
because it also asked,
it asked voters for a second choice.
When you look at whether
one of these candidates
is someone's first or second choice,
Joe Biden has the support
of half the primary voters
and that's with more than
20 people in this race,
Sanders hits 40%,
Elizabeth Warren, as
you can see there, 25%,
Kamala Harris right there as well, 24%.
We have two road warriors
covering two of the biggest movers
in all of these polls right now.
Mike Memoli is covering
the Biden campaign.
He is in Cedar Rapids, Iowa.
Vaughn Hilliard covering
the Harris campaign.
He is in Des Moines, Iowa.
Mike, I'll start with you.
This is Biden's first campaign
rally since those debates,
what's the plan?
- Well Craig there's no doubt that
a lot has changed for the Biden campaign
ahead of what is his third trip to Iowa
since announcing his candidacy in April.
He was behind me here in Cedar Rapids
on that first trip in
April saying at the time
that no one was gonna work harder than him
to win the support of Iowa voters.
That second trip to Iowa about a month ago
you'll remember that he was here
at the same time as President Trump,
it really gave Biden an opportunity
to really frame that
general election matchup,
of course electability being
one of the strongest arguments
that Joe Biden has so far, but as I said
there's no doubt when you
talk to Biden advisors
that they feel the game has changed.
Game on as one advisor said.
You look at some of these polls
that show him slipping after that
shaky debate performance.
A senior Biden campaign advisor
tells me listen we're no more worried
about these latest polls that show
a little bit of a dip,
that we were overconfident
based on those initial
polls that showed him
with a strong lead, but we
are seeing him now recognize
that he can't just stay above the fray
in the terms of running
in the Democratic Primary
and what will be interesting, Craig,
we're gonna see Joe Biden campaigning
on the Fourth of July
tomorrow in Independence, Iowa
at the same time as Beto O'Rourke
another one of his contenders.
Also, Craig, tomorrow night Joe Biden
will also be attending an Iowa Cubs game
also with Beto O'Rourke which means
for me on the Fourth of July I get paid
to attend a minor league baseball game.
Sounds good to me.
- That's true, it's a good point.
Mr. Hillard, I turn to you.
How does the Harris
camp plan to capitalize
on this post-NBC News debate momentum?
Any ideas there?
- Well how they're gonna capitalize,
they're here for three straight
days of campaign events.
She'll be just next
door in West Des Moines
this afternoon and then she'll be
going from Iowa over to New Orleans
and then South Carolina next week.
Essentially she's not going
to let up off the gas.
She's gonna go full forward and this is
part of the campaign's effort to continue
to show the contrast of what Kamala Harris
can bring to the campaign trail.
She plans to go full on,
they now have 65 staffers
here on the ground in Iowa
and as Mike just mentioned, the debate
was a wake up call for the Biden campaign
that he couldn't just stay above the fray
because what last week showed was that
this is going to be a Democratic Primary
in which candidates will
show contrast between them.
Kamala Harris not only on
issues of race and busing,
but also on the Obama
Administration's deportation policies.
I want to play for you
a little bit of sound.
This was actually from
just over a week ago
when Kamala Harris was
over in South Carolina.
I think it's very pertinent to
what we should expect to hear
from the California Senator
today and in the weeks ahead.
- We need somebody who as
President of the United States
understands the need to rebuild the party.
Who understands the need
to give the resources
and the support to the people who are
on the ground everyday
doing the hard work.
We can't just helicopter in here.
We have to support the people who are
on the ground, who know the community.
- Kamala Harris in that
debate made herself vulnerable
to folks, to voters who
said that they are anxious
about Democrats attacking one another,
but what she did at the same time
and what the polls are indicating
she separated herself as a willingness
to paint contrast between her and others
and as you just heard from
her there in South Carolina,
what we should expect to
hear from her here in Iowa
is that she is maintaining
that she is the candidate
that is looking forward and will outwork
the rest of the field, Craig.
- All right, Vaughn Hilliard
there in Des Moines.
Vaughn thank you and Mike
Memoli thank you as well, sir.
Will they or won't they?
A new tweet from President
Trump just moments ago
appears to contradict
his own Administration
on a citizenship question on the census.
We're gonna dig into that,
it's a developing story.
Also, the newest round of
post-NBC News debate polls
suggested some candidates might
be in more trouble when it comes
to reaching the debate stage this fall.
One of those contenders
also hitting the ground
in Iowa this week, Congressman
Tim Ryan will join us ahead.
♪ I want it that way ♪
- I can't believe it.
- That Carl brought his karaoke machine?
♪ Ain't nothing but a heartache ♪
- No, I can't believe how easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
my car insurance with Geico.
♪ Tell me why I never
want to hear you say ♪
- No Kevin!
No Kevin!
No!
- [Announcer] Believe it.
Geico could save you 15%
or more on car insurance.
- [Announcer] Alice loves the scent
of Gain so much she wished they
came in a fabric softener too.
Say hello to your fairy godmother, Alice.
Oh and look they've got Gain scent beads
and dryer sheets too.
- As a real estate agent, I've learned
it's excess moisture
that causes musty odors.
Pro-tip: use DampRid.
- [Announcer] New DampRid drop-in tabs.
Attract and trap excess moisture
out of the air eliminating musty odors.
- Works every time.
- [Announcer] Get rid of dampness.
♪ DampRid ♪
- [Narrator] It all comes down
to a single defining moment.
When a plan stops being a plan
and gets set into motion.
Today's Merrill can help you get there.
With the people, tools,
and personalized advice
to help turn your ambitions into action.
What would you like the power to do?
- Thanks, Golden Corral.
Dan gets his slow-smoked sirloin
and my little trio were as
happy as shrimp, oops, clams,
and mom got it all,
hook, line and sirloin.
The slow-smoked sirloin and shrimp trio.
Golden Corral, the only one for everyone.
- No matter what I wore,
I worried someone might see
my bladder leak underwear.
So I switched to Always Discreet Boutique.
It's shape hugging threads
smooth out the back
so it fits better than
Depend and no one notices.
Always discreet.
- I'm Alex Trebek, here to tell you
about the Colonial Penn program.
If you're age 50 to 85 and looking
to buy life insurance on a fixed budget,
remember the three P's.
- What are the three P's?
- The three P's of life insurance
on a fixed budget are
price, price and price.
A price you can afford,
a price that can't increase,
and a price that fits your budget.
- I'm 65 and take
medications, what's my price?
- You can get coverage for $9.95 a month.
- I just turned 80, what's my price?
- 9.95 a month for you too.
If you're age 50 to 85,
call now about the number one most popular
whole life insurance plan available
through the Colonial Penn program.
It has an affordable rate
starting at $9.95 a month.
No medical exam, no health questions,
your acceptance is guaranteed,
and this plan has a
guaranteed lifetime rate lock
so your rate can never
go up for any reason
and with this plan you can pick
your payment date, so you can time
your premium due date to
work with your budget.
So call now for free information
and you'll also get this
free Beneficiary Planner
and it's yours just for calling.
So call now.
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-775-7230
for your free information
and your free gift.
That number again is 1-800-775-7230.
Call now.
- Moments ago President
Trump took to Twitter
to say that he will defy
his own Justice Department
and the courts on the Census.
The President says that the census
will have a citizenship question.
NBC White House
correspondent Kelly O'Donnell
is here to try and clear this up.
Hey Kelly O, Justice Department says no,
President says yes.
What do we know about what's happening?
- Well it's a little more complicated
and what this really gets down to
is the president does
not like this decision
and this of course as the president
who argues forcefully that
asking those who reply
to the 2020 Census if
they are American citizens
is an important piece of data,
along with all the other
things that a census collects.
What we learned late Tuesday, yesterday,
was that the Department of Justice
and the Department of Commerce
were going forward with printing
of the 2020 questionnaire
without the citizenship question.
Now is there some gray area here?
You can keep a legal challenge going
which the president is arguing for here,
and at the same time
take the pragmatic step
of printing the new census
and doing it lawfully
without that citizenship question now
because of the enormity of the task
of doing the 2020 Census.
So what we need some clarification on is,
is the president directly
defying this plan to print
or is he arguing for
continuing the legal case
which of course the Supreme
Court had pushed it back
to the lower court and said the reasons
given by the Department of Commerce,
Secretary Wilbur Ross, were not sufficient
to argue for adding this question
and it was an open opportunity
for the Administration to keep litigating,
but they're running up
against a time deadline
because the Constitution,
not just any ordinary law,
but the Constitution
requires that a census
be taken every 10 years.
So, we're up against that deadline.
So is it pragmatism meets politics,
is it a frustrated president who's been
active on Twitter today pushing back
this decision by the Department of Justice
and Commerce that we
learned about late yesterday
really followed within 24 hours
of the president arguing pretty forcefully
that he wanted to keep fighting this
and so the president has
sort of been pushed back
on his heels with this.
He's calling it fake news.
We have officials in both
departments who told us
the plan is to go forward
with the printing.
So is he advocating for
the court case to go on?
Is this just sort of a political
message from the president,
to our understanding the
census question will not,
the citizenship question is not
in the new printing that will
be ordered fairly shortly.
Craig.
- Kelly O'Donnell from the White House,
for us, Kelly O, thank you.
I'm joined now by Senior Correspondent
for NPR Boston and MSNBC
Contributor, Kimberly Atkins.
Also with me, Assistant
Professor of Public Policy
at Harvard University,
Leah Wright Rigueur.
Thank you ladies both for being with me.
Leah let me start with you,
just your general reaction
to this new tweet on the census.
Apparently the printer's already
been instructed to start the process, so.
What's going on here?
- So there are a lot of different issues
that are going on here.
First we see again that the president
is completely at odds with other factions
or other agencies or
divisions, departments
within his own administration.
So it raises the question,
who's in charge here,
who's running the show?
The other thing too that I think
is important to keep in mind is that
the president is essentially saying,
and this may be saber rattling,
it may just be trying to
send a hard political message
and showing his base
that he means business
or it may actually be serious,
but he's essentially saying
I'm gonna go against this
and I'm gonna go against
the court's rulings,
I'm gonna go against my
own Justice Department
and I'm going to ensure that that question
finds its way on there.
So in some way, shape, or form,
he is promising to really uphold
the question about citizenship
and change the census.
Now can he do that?
It's not exactly clear
how he would do that,
but he's essentially promising to do that
and that is cause for concern.
- You know what, Kimberly,
I think for folks
who are watching and who are listening
on Sirius Satellite Radio
who perhaps haven't been
following this story as closely,
maybe we should remind them why is it
that this president finds this
citizenship question itself.
Why does he want this
to be part of the census
so very badly?
- Well it's a couple of political reasons
for this, Craig.
One is that when the citizenship question
is on the census there is research
that would say that it would actually work
to suppress participation in the census
and get an under count,
particularly not just of
people who are immigrants,
but even citizens who
are related to immigrants
have folks who are of
mixed immigration status
within their household.
There will be a fear that
participating in this census
could somehow flag them or
get them in sort of trouble.
We have seen through documentation
throughout the litigation over this census
that there are some folks who know
that that would hurt
Democrats in an election.
I mean the census decides a lot of things
from Congressional districts
to federal funding,
but it will have an
impact on the election.
Could depress turn out
and depress the strength
of Democratic districts.
So there's a political incentive here.
I've talked to state
officials who have said
even with the census
question not on the census,
there has been so much discussion,
so much divisiveness over this issue
that they are still fearing
that there will be an under count
and that will be
problematic for these states
who depend on the census
for their federal funding.
- Also in the news today, of course,
these troubling images that we are getting
thanks to that Watchdog group
of the migrant detention centers
from inside these migrant
detention centers.
I asked presidential hopeful Jay Inslee
just a few moments ago about
his plan for immigration
and we also talked about
President Trump's strategy
on immigration.
Leah, Kimberly, this is what he said.
- He has made it very clear that he wants
to make people afraid and he likes
these inhumane conditions because it is
part of his intention to
fan the flame of discord
around immigration and
instead of uniting us
to find a comprehensive solution,
instead of trying to
address the root causes
of this immigration problem to keep people
where they live and not
force them to come north,
he has decided to utilize
inhumane conditions
as a tool of his gross cruelty.
- Leah, is what we're seeing,
is it the president's strategy,
or is the result of a failed strategy?
- So, the answer is yes to both.
I think one of the things that
has emerged and has emerged
over the past couple of years
is that the Trump Administration
has been very, very direct in some ways,
in some ways not so direct,
but has been pretty direct about saying
that their separation policies,
their policies around the border,
these policies about detention
centers have been designed
to dissuade people from
coming to the border.
It has not been successful
and because it has not been successful,
we have seen an explosion
in kind of these centers,
these areas and then kind
of very poor conditions
and we've seen the Administration arguing
in favor of poor conditions.
Now the bigger thing I think
and this is going to be
a question for many of
the Democratic candidates
moving into primary debates
and into the general election
is well what are you gonna do about it?
What are we going to do to fix it?
What is the actual policy agenda
both on immigration, on refugee sedum,
on asylum seekers and then the conditions
that these people are facing
because right now this is unsustainable
and as a political strategy
perhaps it's working
for President Trump's supporters,
but for the rest of the country
it absolutely is not working.
- Kimberly, let's talk
politics for just a second here
and Mayor Pete specifically,
we were just talking
about his fundraising numbers
during our last segment.
Bernie Sanders as well
put up about 24 million,
actually Bernie Sanders
transferred about six million.
He raised roughly 18,
but Mayor Pete raised
close to $25 million.
That's pretty impressive
for a second quarter,
but you look at his polling
and the two don't seem to make sense.
Why is he not polling better
if he is raising so much money?
- Well a few reasons, I've
been talking to people
who are raising money for Mayor Pete
as he travels to places
including Massachusetts
this upcoming weekend and they say
that on the ground he is
resonating with folks,
they're doing a combination of
these big dollar fundraisers that
folks like Elizabeth
Warren and Bernie Sanders
have chosen not to do, but also doing
the smaller dollar donations in order
to energize younger people, really allow
people to get to know him and it has been
literally paying off.
Now one thing that
raising this money will do
will allow him to stay in the race longer
than some of the other candidates
and give him more of an opportunity
to build his profile, get out with ads,
and raise his profile.
I think a lot of people just don't know
who he is or what he's about yet
and that could happen,
but on the other hand
he's had a particularly
difficult time resonating
with voters of color.
We know that for Democrats,
that is a crucial, crucial block.
He had the issue with the police shooting
in South Bend and so that is a big,
that's a big obstacle that he's going
to have to overcome, but at least for now
he has the funds to stay in it.
- Kimberly Atkins, Leah Wright Rigor,
enjoy the holiday, ladies,
thank you for your time.
Thank you, thank you.
- Thank you.
- He's been extremely vocal about winning
back those voters that swung to Trump.
Now, Congressman Tim Ryan sounding off
on the effect that the immigration debate
could have on the race.
Congressman Ryan joins me after the break.
(soft music)
- [Narrator] Nothing feels like connecting
with the people that matter.
Holiday Inn, Holiday Inn Express.
We're there.
So you can be too.
- [Announcer] This is the
box that started it all.
The box that changed how
people buy mattresses forever.
This is the mattress so comfortable
people can't stop giving it five stars.
(upbeat music)
This is Casper.
The company bringing bedtime back
to millions of happy sleepers.
One box at a time.
Try America's number one rated mattress
for 100 nights, risk free.
- [Announcer] Enjoy 10% off
your order at Casper.com.
- Introducing Nutrisystem's
July Fourth sale.
Save 50%, yes 50%.
- [Announcer] Lose up to 13 pounds
and seven inches in you first month.
Order your 28 day plan and get
one week of high protein shakes
with probiotics to help
shrink your belly free.
- And there's even a money back guarantee.
- [Announcer] Save 50% off every program.
- Grab this special offer right now
and start losing today.
- [Announcer] Go online
or call 877-651-FIT6
right now to save 50%.
(light music)
- [Narrator] There is a place
where you can make up for lost time
by completely losing track of it.
Where you can indulge in everything
because it's all included.
(upbeat music)
Sandals, the world's only five
star luxury included resorts.
Call 1-800-Sandals.
- Hi Phil Swift here for the
flex seal family of products.
Now all the strength of
original Flex Seal is available
in portable, powerful minis.
From the toughest jobs to a simple repair,
Flex Minis are always there.
Now with Flex Minis you can grab and go.
Plus they're freakin' adorable.
Whether it's Flex tape,
Flex glue, or Flex Seal,
imagine everything you
could do with Flex Minis.
- I have one kid in each
branch of the military,
but I'm command central.
- [Announcer] Why Elaine choose Verizon.
- It's so important to us that Verizon
is supporting military families.
When I have a child deployed
having a reliable
network means everything.
So when I get a video chat
and I get to see their face,
it's the best thing in the world
and I've earned every
one of these gray hairs.
Military moms, we serve too.
- [Announcer] The network
more people rely on
gives you more, like military plans
with a special price on unlimited,
$100 per line and big savings
on our best phones when you switch.
That's Verizon.
- Think all premium fuels are the same?
New Shell V-Power NiTRO+ Premium Gasoline
is engineered with four levels of defense
against gunk, wear,
corrosion and friction.
That helps keep your
engine running like new.
(bell dings)
(crowd cheers)
So maybe it's time to unthink
what you think you think
about premium fuel.
Shell V-Power NiTRO+ Premium Gasoline
It's fuel for thought.
- [Lester] Good evening,
everyone, breaking news tonight.
- [Announcer] Lester Holt.
- [Lester] It sounds like
a jet airplane up there,
but that is fire.
- [Announcer] The most trusted
TV news anchor in America.
- [Lester] That's Nightly
News, I'm Lester Holt.
- [Announcer] More
America's watch NBC News
than any other news
organization in the world.
- Democrats are focused on making
the overcrowded and dangerous conditions
revealed in these migrant
detention facilities
a national focal point.
I'm joined now by Ohio
Democratic Congressman
and presidential candidate, Tim Ryan.
Congressman, we have all
seen these pictures now
and we've heard some of
the heartbreaking stories
of the conditions from these
migrant detention facilities.
A number of the other candidates
have visited and released
some detailed plans
on how to deal with them.
I don't believe you've
done either just yet.
What would you do?
What would you do with
these detention facilities,
specifically facilities
that are privately operated?
Go ahead.
- Yeah, we should not be
locking these people up
and the way we're doing
it, Craig, is atrocious.
I think it goes against our values.
I think we need to make sure,
I wish the president would
ask doctors and nurses
to go immediately to the border
and start helping administer some care
to these people.
Jamming them in these facilities,
I mean this is this stunning to think
that this is the United States of America
and it's contributing
to the level of anxiety
that we have across our
society today, Craig.
I mean, everyone's telling us things
are going really good,
but yet everybody feels really bad
and this anxiety that just
watching these things happen,
let alone if you're in anyway connected
to these people that are down there
is just heartbreaking and
we're the United States,
we should be able to go
down there and fix this
and it shouldn't take that long.
- What would you do on day one if elected?
About this specifically?
- Well make sure everybody coming in
through these facilities is taken care of,
but the key's gonna be
to go to Central America
and actually stabilize those countries
where people are migrating from.
The president is the Distractor in Chief.
He can't focus for more than five seconds.
The issue is in Central America.
I've been saying this now for months.
We need to go to Central America,
stabilize those countries,
kick the gangs out.
We don't even have an
Ambassador in Honduras right now
so we can't be engaged
in the way we want to be
and the president is cutting
the State Department funding
that would help us repair
what's happening down there,
that's the heart of the problem,
that's where people are coming from
and if we want to end
the crisis at the border
we need to go deal with
heart of the matter
in Central America.
- Like a number of the candidates
over the holiday weekend
here, you are in Iowa,
you're in Iowa right now,
Waterloo.
- Yeah.
- There is a new Suffolk
University USA Today poll
of Iowa voters from after
NBC's debate last week.
This poll just out, USA
Today put it this way.
Three of those who
participated in the debates,
New York Mayor Bill de Blasio,
Ohio Representative Tim Ryan,
and California
Representative Eric Swalwell
failed to attract a single supporter
in the Iowa survey.
That's of 500 people in Iowa
who were surveyed, Congressman.
Do you have what it takes
to stay in this race?
- No doubt about it.
I mean literally our
phone has been ringing
off the hook since the debate.
We've got a lot of
people that we're leaning
to Vice President Biden
who were calling us
and they want to meet primarily
from the early states.
We've had some of the
best fundraising days
we've had since the debate.
So I think we connected.
I mean clearly the national conversation
was around something different and I think
these polls at this point
are absolutely meaningless.
I mean, you can go back
and look at winners
from the last 40 years
and at some point they were where I am now
and I think we've got the message.
We're connecting with
people around the stress
and anxiety and fear that's facing them
whether it's the economic anxiety,
whether it's around healthcare,
whether it's around what we're watching
happen at the border,
whether it's what's happening
to our environment and our soil
and the things that are
happening environmentally.
We're connecting with people, Craig,
and people are, you
know, I'm asking people
to come to TimRyanforAmerica.com,
be a part of this campaign.
We just released the most comprehensive
transformational education agenda
to help with trauma-based
care for our kids
and social and emotional learning
in our schools and wraparound therapy,
so we are taking care of the big issues
in my campaign and that's why
people are getting on board.
- You just mentioned fundraising.
How much have you raised
in the second quarter?
- Well we don't have, I don't
have the numbers right now,
but I will tell you--
- Ballpark it.
- Our best days were
right after the debate
and I was really excited about that
and we've done really well into July
so we're moving in the right direction.
I mean I didn't get in till April.
- 24 million?
- So.
We're moving in the right direction.
I'm really pleased with it.
- Mayor Pete's at about
24, almost 25 million.
Bernie Sanders put out his
numbers yesterday at 24 million.
Are we in that neighborhood?
- We are not in that neighborhood.
I mean here's the deal, Craig.
I'm from Northeast Ohio.
I'm not from a big city.
I'm not from a big state.
I don't have an Ivy League education
or network that I can tap into.
So, we're you know doing it the way
the way it has to be done
and that's grassroots,
building this thing brick by brick,
but we're moving in the right direction.
We got people excited.
We just started a whole
Teacher's for Tim initiative
around teacher's who are coming on board.
So we're building this thing out.
I mean it's important
to remember it's July,
Bill Clinton didn't get in this race
when he ran in '92 till October.
So we are way ahead of the game here
compared to past years.
- Congressman, thank you
and enjoy the Fourth.
Thank you very much.
Ahead in the next hour,
my colleague Andrea
Mitchell's gonna have more
on the controversy
surrounding the president's
planned Fourth of July event.
D.C.'s Mayor, Muriel Bowser will join her.
- Budget meeting!
- Sweet.
- When you compare last
quarter to this quarter.
- [Announcer] It's no wonder everything
seems a little better with
the creamy taste of Philly,
made with fresh milk and real cream.
It must be the Philly.
- When you book at Hilton.com
you get the price match guarantee.
So if you find your room at a lower rate,
Hilton is like we're gonna match that rate
and give you an extra 25% off.
- What would travel sites do
if you found a different price?
- That's not my problem it's your problem.
Book at hilton.com.
- [Announcer] Not getting enough cash back
with that credit card?
Turn to the nerds.
Looking for the perfect mortgage?
Oops! (laughs)
Sorry about that.
Easily compare credit cards, mortgages,
savings accounts and
more at nerdwallet.com.
- Oh, wrong move.
Old fashioned bandages get dirty.
They can let in water and germs.
Look, it's falling off.
New-Skin is the flexible liquid bandage
that seals out the bad stuff.
There's a spray too.
- [Announcer] New-Skin,
re-think how you heal.
- [Announcer] Congratulations,
you're a writer,
but, wait, you have to
actually publish your book.
Discover Publishers will
help you find the right
publisher to get your book in bookstores.
It's completely free.
- [Announcer] Go to
freeauthorinfo.com or call us
at 800-251-4119.
- [Announcer] Men, want to
feel younger, stronger, leaner?
You don't have to slow down after 40.
New Nugenix Total-T is our most powerful,
man-boosting formula ever.
To get a complimentary bottle,
text 369369 and enter POP.
- [Announcer] Paying too
much for your prescriptions.
- Isn't this a situation of hate the game
not the player?
- This is a power play.
This is a strategic move from her right?
- Why is this potentially such a big deal?
- We have more breaking news.
Why wouldn't we?
It's Tuesday in Washington.
- The wall is the sticking
point, not border.