- Is one debate, I suggest you open up
and begin reading it or
next time you're asked
don't profess to be one
that practices that,
and at least learn one or two verses
that mean something to you.
Because maybe all of it, as you said,
was what your favorite is is too much
for you to consume and
practice at the same time.
That does it for me,
thanks for watching,
I'll see you back here
next Saturday at 5:00 p.m. Eastern.
Until then keep the conversation going,
like us at Facebook.com/politicsnation,
and follow us on Twitter @politicsnation.
Up next, Meet the Press with Chuck Todd.
- [Chuck] This Sunday, divided Democrats.
Bernie versus Biden,
progressives versus traditional Democrats,
highlighted by this comment
from freshman Congresswoman Ilhan Omar.
- I want to talk about
the political influence
in this country
that says it is okay for people to push
for allegiance to a foreign country.
- [Chuck] Some fellow
Democrats hear bigotry.
- The use of anti-Semitic language
and images can never be tolerated.
- [Chuck] Others rush to her defense.
- What I hear is her trying
to uplift my grandmother
in Palestine, in the West Bank.
- [Chuck] The debate
exposing real fissures
in the Democratic Party
with implications for 2020.
My guests this morning,
Democratic Senator Sherrod Brown of Ohio
and Representative Liz Cheney,
chair of the House Republican Conference.
Plus, waiting for Biden,
Sherrod Brown not running,
Michael Bloomberg not
running, both likely out,
because they expect Joe Biden to get in.
- I have not made the final decision.
But don't be surprised.
- [Chuck] So what is Biden waiting for?
And pardon me?
Did Michael Cohen ask
President Trump for a pardon?
- I have never asked for,
nor would I accept, a pardon.
- And that's a stone-cold lie.
- I'll talk about that,
the surprise Manafort sentencing,
and the latest on the Russia investigation
with the chair of the House
Intelligence Committee,
Adam Schiff.
Joining me for insight and analysis are
NBC News Capitol Hill
correspondent Kasie Hunt;
Robert Costa, moderator
of Washington Week on PBS;
Maria Teresa Kumar,
president of Voto Latino;
and the former Republican
governor of North Carolina,
Pat McCrory.
Welcome to Sunday.
It's Meet the Press.
- [Dennis] From NBC News in Washington,
the longest-running show
in television history.
This is Meet the Press with Chuck Todd.
- Good Sunday morning.
Never mind that President
Trump's campaign chairman
is going to prison and that Mr. Trump
and Michael Cohen argued this
week over which one of them
is lying about a possible pardon.
Our colleague, Dana Milbank
at The Washington Post,
pointed out that with President Trump's
recent struggles on North
Korea, on the trade deficit,
on the border wall, there's only one thing
that can save him, the Democrats.
And as he said, right
on cue, here they come.
Democrats have spent
much of the last month
wrestling themselves to the ground.
They were embarrassed over the revelation
that Virginia Governor Ralph Northam
had once dressed in blackface,
startled by subsequent
accusations of sexual assault
against Northam's lieutenant
governor, Justin Fairfax,
and chronically unsure, this week,
over how to handle a comment
by freshman Democrat Ilhan Omar,
her second that many saw as anti-Semitic.
An emerging, more-progressive
cohort of elected Democrats
is coming into conflict
with an older generation of centrists
and traditional liberals.
These two Democratic factions
are united and divided.
They're united about the urgency
of defeating President Trump next year.
But at the same time, they are divided,
with each side seeing the other
as the reason Mr. Trump may
wind up winning, after all.
- You apologized for your last remarks.
How are these different?
- [Chuck] Congresswoman Ilhan Omar
drew criticism after tweeting
that U.S. politicians
support Israel, because,
"It's all about the Benjamins, baby."
She apologized but then
made this comment last week.
- Jews have dual loyalty and
can't be patriotic members
of the country in which they live?
Words matter.
- [Chuck] Some progressives defended Omar,
pointing to anti-Muslim slurs against her,
like this flier in West Virginia.
- We think that hate and racism
in our country is growing,
no matter if you're Jewish, LGBTQ, Latino,
immigrant, Muslim.
- [Chuck] Late this week,
House Democrats united
around a broad resolution
condemning hate, after
some progressives objected
to an initial draft that
only rebuked anti-Semitism.
The episode is among those
dividing 2020 Democrats.
- [Chuck] But several top
presidential candidates,
while condemning anti-Semitism,
said Omar was unfairly targeted.
The debate is exposing
ideological, generational,
and racial divides in
the Democratic Party,
as the progressive left
is showing its strength.
- It is time to break up
America's tech giants.
- [Chuck] Some 2020
Democrats are reluctant
to embrace capitalism.
- You know, again, the labels,
I'm not sure any of them fit.
- [Chuck] Championing the Green New Deal.
- Does the Green New Deal go too far?
- No, you cannot go too far on
the issue of climate change.
- [Chuck] And calling
for Medicare for All.
- Do you think eliminating
private insurance
would be a socialist idea?
- No okay, so I strongly believe
that we need to have Medicare for All.
- [Chuck] Can a more centrist candidate
break through in a party
that is shifting to the left?
- Why should we elect
a candidate who says,
no, that's not possible,
to do everything progressives want?
- Because I'm being honest.
- [Chuck] This week,
both former New York City
Mayor Michael Bloomberg
and Ohio Senator Sherrod
Brown said, no thanks,
to a presidential run,
with former Vice President Joe Biden
poised to jump into the race.
- I have not made the final decision.
But don't be surprised.
- [Chuck] Even before his run is official,
Biden is already explaining
a decades-long record,
including his role in passing
the now-controversial 1994 Crime Bill,
his vote for the Iraq war,
skepticism of Anita Hill,
and past comments on busing
to desegregate schools.
- You know, I've been in
this fight for a long time.
I haven't always been right.
I know we haven't always
gotten things right.
But I've always tried.
- And joining me now from Cleveland,
is Democratic Senator
Sherrod Brown of Ohio,
who announced this week,
to the surprise of many,
that he had decided not to
run for president in 2020.
Senator Brown, welcome back
to Meet the Press, Senator.
- Good to be back, thanks.
- Color us very surprised.
In fact, the last time you were on,
my executive producer noted,
he was speaking about
his presidential campaign
in the present tense.
It was so, it seemed so imminent to us.
So you did surprise a lot of people.
You had even begun to hire some people.
What changed your mind?
- Well, as you know, Chuck,
this all started off,
because I don't think
Democrats were talking
to working-class Americans
of all races enough.
If you love your country,
you fight for the people who make it work.
We began our Dignity of
Work tour in four states.
Yes, we hired people to
help us with that tour
and to be ready.
And that our goal was
to inform the narrative,
in the Democratic Party,
so that Democrats begin
to talk more to workers
and talk about the dignity of work.
A number of candidates
have already done that,
have been talking about
the dignity of work.
I predict that the Democratic nominee
is the one that talks to workers the best.
And I'm not just talking about workers
in the industrial Midwest.
I'm talking about the
physical therapist in Nevada,
and the construction
worker in New Hampshire
and the hospital worker in Baltimore.
And I would predict, if I could do this,
that come January 20, 2021,
that, in the inaugural,
when either when the
Democratic president elect
raises her or his right hand,
they will launch into a speech.
Their inaugural speech will
talk about the dignity of work.
Because it's not just a slogan.
It's who I am, it's what we fight for.
But most importantly, it's how we govern
in the end.
- Actually,
to reinforce what you're saying,
we put together a collection of folks
that stole your line, take a listen.
- We have to reward and recognize
the dignity of work, right?
- There is dignity in all
work and career professionals.
- We've got to give it
the dignity of the work
that is being performed.
- So Senator, your message, in some ways,
you're doing something that
many presidential candidates
wish could've happened to them.
Your initial message begins to resonate
to the point where you've got competitors
stealing your lines.
So let me ask you this,
how do you not run?
It was resonating and you still said, no.
- Well, it was resonating.
And I'd say, mission accomplished.
But I'm not done yet.
I can do that better now from the Senate.
I mean we spent three months talking about
the dignity of work.
I'll continue to do that.
I went to the floor,
right after I announced
I wasn't going to run and
talked about civil rights
and voting rights and worker rights
and a Supreme Court that puts its thumb
on the scales of justice
in favoring corporations
over workers and health
insurance companies
over sick people and Wall
Street over consumers.
I will continue that
economic-populist fight,
always through the eyes of workers.
It's what we are as a party.
I think I can drive that
better from the Senate
than I can as one out of 15,
20 presidential candidates.
But in that sense, we're--
- When was the last,
I'm curious.
When was the last time
you talked to Joe Biden?
- October.
- So you haven't talked to him recently.
This wasn't him calling around,
letting people know he's running.
- It was none of that.
I know that that's been reported.
But the people that reported
that never called me,
never called Connie, never
called Sarah Benzing,
my chief of staff,
never called Jenny, my
communications director.
I like Joe Biden.
I just haven't talked to him.
And people ask me, in almost
every one of these states,
is Joe Biden getting in having
any impact on your decision?
And my answer was always, zero.
- So when people were
assessing your candidacy,
you were seen as one of these folks
that could bridge this divide.
You're a guy that figured out how to win
in a red state but also had kept
to some progressive principles.
In fact, here's what you told The Nation
in an interview very recently,
just before you decided not to run.
You said, "If I run,
I'll be the only Democrat
"on the stage who will have
voted against the Iraq War,
"who will have voted against
the Defense of Marriage Act,"
which means "and for marriage equality,
"and who will be pro-choice,
100%, over the years."
What was interesting
there, it seemed to me,
it was your way of saying, hey,
I'm an experienced Democrat.
But I'm also on the
progressive side of the lane
in ways that other Democrats,
perhaps you're referring
to Joe Biden, were not.
- I was referring to nobody in particular.
I was just saying that I've been
a strong progressive for years.
I will carry that back to the Senate.
I will be part of this
presidential campaign,
in terms of calling out this president
for his phony populism.
Populism is never racist and anti-Semitic.
Populism doesn't divide people.
Populists don't give tax cuts
to the richest people in the country
and then try to cut
Medicare and Head Start.
And I will point out how this president
has betrayed the auto workers in Lordstown
and betrayed hospital workers in Van Wert.
And I will continue to make that case
from the floor of the Senate,
from travels around the country,
by not yet supporting any
presidential candidate
but moving the debate forward
about dignity of work.
- But let me ask you this.
Do you think there's a danger
of going too far to the left,
that it might scare some
voters, say, in Ohio?
- Well, I hear these stories that are,
that's the story of the day,
about Democrats moving to the left.
I think the more important story
is how Republicans continue
to move to the right.
How President Trump betrays workers
and utters racist anti-Semitic rhetoric.
And nobody in their party calls him out.
They don't have divisions.
They've all followed his racist actions
and betrayal of workers.
They've followed it like
lemmings off the cliff.
That's the story, not some
degrees of differences
between and among Democrats.
That's the real story.
- Let me ask you this,
though, what is fair game?
You, in that interview,
had said, hey, in 1996,
essentially, when it wasn't
a popular thing to do,
you voted against the Defense
of Marriage Act, for instance.
Joe Biden has comments about busing
and desegregation of
schools that are popping up,
some quotes from him in the '70s.
You could make an argument,
that was the mainstream,
Democratic Party position,
perhaps, in the '70s.
Should those comments
matter to voters in Iowa,
to Democrats in Iowa, in the 21st century?
- Well, it doesn't really
matter what Chuck Todd
or Sherrod Brown thinks
about whether they matter
to voters in Iowa.
- Do they matter to you?
- Well, it matters, records matter to me.
The candidate that is
talking, I mean, I go back to,
what are they going to do
about talking to workers
and the dignity of work?
I want to see dignity of work
not just part of this
campaign, not just a slogan,
not just who these candidates,
what these candidates talk about.
I want to make sure they govern
based on the dignity of work.
And, and so regardless of
the kind of work you do,
whether it's about wages,
it's about benefits,
it's about workplace safety,
it's about childcare.
In Nevada, in the Culinary
Workers Union Hall in Las Vegas,
Connie and I were there
three or four weeks ago,
their slogan is, one job should be enough.
I want to hear workers
start talking about that,
that one living wage job should be enough,
with healthcare, with
retirement, with childcare,
with safety in the workplace.
That's everything to me in this race,
and that's a winning message.
And it's the way we should
govern, starting in 2021.
- Senator, I'm going to
close with the same question
I asked you at the beginning.
I still didn't really hear an
answer for why you didn't run.
Is it simply you didn't want to do it?
- I think we were successful
in moving forward, as we have.
You know I was talking to
some people about this.
And you know, you can
run three different ways.
You can run as Eeyore, where
you get up every day and,
oh my god, I gotta to do this.
And I didn't want to be that.
You can run as the angry candidate.
I didn't want to be that.
Or you can run as the sort of
optimist, joyful candidate,
the way I try to do my job in the Senate.
I think I can do that
better in the Senate,
in continuing to inform
this presidential race.
- Senator, you're saying you can't
run for president joyfully.
That's quite the, that's
what I just heard.
Sorry I mean that's--
- I think I can do it,
I think I can do it better in the Senate.
- Fair enough.
- Leave it at that, Chuck.
- Senator Sherrod Brown.
- Your show, it's always
joyful, being on your show.
- Well, that, I appreciate.
It's Sunday morning, cup of coffee,
and you've sprung forward.
That, I appreciate.
- Even when the time changes,
and you make me get up an hour earlier.
- Senator, I will leave it there.
- And then you broadcast it later.
And people don't know how
early we got up so, on Sunday.
Anyway, thank you, Chuck.
- Man,
you and your Ohio colleague
John Kasich, man, you guys,
you guys know how to
talk to your Ohio voters.
Thank you, sir.
- All right thanks.
- Much appreciated.
- Joining me now is the chair
of the House Republican Conference,
Liz Cheney of Wyoming.
Congresswoman Cheney, welcome
back to Meet the Press.
- Thank you, Todd, great
to be back with you.
- I want to start with
what happened in the House this week
because it was a bit of a surprise.
You voted against this broad resolution.
And while your criticism of the resolution
I totally understand, but
you were in the minority
in your party.
Did your fellow House Republicans
make a mistake by voting
with the Democrats
on this resolution?
- No, look, I think
that there were two ways
we could have gone.
Some of the people in our conference
clearly looked at it and said,
there's nothing objectionable
in the resolution.
My statement made clear that
that was my view as well.
But I decided to vote against it
because I think it was
really clearly an effort
to actually protect Ilhan Omar,
to cover up her bigotry and anti-Semitism
by refusing to name her.
The Democrats have yet to take any action
to remove her from her committee.
And they've got a real problem.
I mean, the extent to which they are now
abiding by anti-Semitism,
enabling anti-Semitism in their party
is something we watched them struggle with
but something that's very
dangerous for the country.
So I'm hopeful that they will be able
to stand up and do the
right thing on this.
- I am curious, there
was a bit of criticism.
Politico noted their "Republican
sources were quite peeved
"at Cheney," referring to you,
"to say the least.
"The thinking among most
top Republicans is this.
"When you're part of a leadership team,
"you stick together, period."
Criticism being since you're
a member of leadership,
that you should have
spoken with one voice.
- Well, look, I think that, you know,
you know how the Hill works.
There are always those anonymous sources
who are out there sniping.
But I think the important
thing for us to be focused on
and to remember,
the Democrats have been in charge now
for about two and a half
months in the House.
And in that time they've become
the party of anti-Semitism,
the party of infanticide,
the party of socialism.
They've passed legislation that's violated
the First Amendment, the Second Amendment.
It's really time for the Democrats,
the leadership in that party
to stop it, to stand up,
and to act worthy frankly of the trust
the American people have placed in them.
It's crucial for the nation.
- I want to unpack a couple
things you just said there.
First on the issue of, you said you think
Congresswoman Omar should lose
her committee assignments.
You led the fight to get
Congressman Steve King,
a Republican,
to have him stripped of
his committee assignment.
Let me ask you this.
Why is this, why should
congressional leaders do that?
If the voters are going
to send these folks,
the voters in western
Iowa know Steve King,
for better or for worse.
And the voters in Minnesota knew,
her comments were very,
very much well publicized.
If they send them there,
should congressional
leaders really be stripping,
not allowing them on committees?
- Yeah, you know, I think the point is
voters send them there.
Nobody is saying we're
going to expel them.
We respect the decision
the voters have made.
But there are certain things
that shouldn't be part
of our public discourse.
White supremacy is one of those.
And anti-Semitism, the history in terms of
what happens when you
don't stand up to the evil,
the history in terms of how quickly
words turn into something
much more horrible
when it comes to anti-Semitism,
as a nation we must at
all times stand up to it.
And the kind of anti-Semitism
that you're seeing now from Ilhan Omar
and that has been
supported by her colleagues
is the kind of anti-Semitism
that really has the ability to creep in
and become normalized in our discourse.
And we have an absolute
obligation not to let that happen.
- Well, there's actually anti-Semitism
that has crept into our discourse.
Look at George Soros, okay?
The Republican and conservative attacks
on George Soros over the years.
In fact, Kevin McCarthy
had to pull one tweet
that implied that he was essentially
trying to buy this or buy that.
That's gotten mainstreamed
in ways for years
to the point where
George Soros had some guy
that was trying to pipe bomb him.
This whataboutism.
- No, no, no, no.
- Can I just say that Congresswoman
this whataboutism.
- Whataboutism, yeah no.
- That everybody tries to
point to the other side.
- Chuck, Chuck.
- And it's getting a little old.
- The whataboutism
absolutely should not go on.
And everyone, including Leader McCarthy,
has stood up absolutely firmly
to condemn anti-Semitism.
The thing that people need
to be focused on here though
is that the Democrats in
the House of Representatives
and even some of the Democrats themselves
are completely frustrated with the fact
that the leadership is,
they are protecting her.
You know, this isn't just being silent.
They are protecting her
by failing to put a
resolution on the floor
that names her and that strips
of her committee assignment.
Instead, they put a
resolution on the floor
which she then went out and said,
"This is a tremendous victory for me."
Now if we are not going to be
in a position where you say
the kind of language that she has said
again, and again, and again
is absolutely unacceptable
and has no place in our discourse, then,
then those people who won't
condemn it are enabling it.
- There was concern by singling her out
you only make her a
target and they pointed
to that West Virginia
Republican Party flier.
- Chuck, I'm sorry, but you don't.
- This is getting, but my point is
we are getting--
- You can describe it
that way, Chuck.
You can describe it that way
- A very dangerous way though,
if we do it.
- But you're wrong.
- You can describe it that
way but you are wrong.
When you have a situation in this country
and around the world where we have seen
a global rise in anti-Semitic attacks,
when we have had the kinds of attacks
that you had on the synagogue
here in the United States recently,
that is a moment when you absolutely--
- A motive on the right.
That guy was motivated by right-wing
fringe ideology.
- Absolutely was anti-Semitic.
- [Chuck] Right.
- Anti-Semitic no matter
where it comes from is wrong.
And when you're in a situation
where you are an elected official,
where we are in a situation where we have
the history that we have,
what happens when you
don't stand up and say,
this is evil, and call it what it is,
we all have an obligation to do that.
And I think it is absolutely
shameful that Nancy Pelosi,
and Leader Hoyer, and
the Democratic leaders
will not put her name in
a resolution on the floor,
and condemn her remarks,
and remove her from the House
Foreign Affairs Committee.
- Do you feel comfortable
that President Trump's
done enough to tamp down
this right-wing fringe
anti-Semitism that's been rising up?
- I don't believe this is right or left.
I think that this is an issue on which
all of us should come together,
particularly elected
officials, the president,
the vice president, members of the Senate
and the House no matter
what your party is.
Stand up and say in today's world
when anti-Semitism is on the rise,
when we have the history that we have,
when we know what happens
when people remain silent,
every single one of us must
at all times stand against it.
- There's a couple of
foreign policy headlines
I wanted to get at you.
First, this was the president
on Friday about North Korea.
- I have a feeling that
our relationship with North
Korea, Kim Jong-un and myself,
Chairman Kim, I think
it's a very good one.
I think it remains good.
I would be surprised in a negative way
if he did anything that was
not per our understanding.
- This is what we've
learned just this week.
He's accelerating the
rocket program again.
He's enriched more uranium
between the two summits.
And more importantly,
they were reconstituting the programs
while the second summit was taking place.
- Yeah.
- With the president there.
You can't take him at his
word on this, can you?
- We have watched Kim
Jong-un, and his father,
and his grandfather operate
the same way now for decades.
And I would say that Republican
and Democratic administrations
got taken by him.
I hope this president won't.
I think that, you know, their
efforts are absolutely clear.
- Hasn't he already gotten
more out of this president
by simply getting respect
on the world stage?
- No, you know what,
I think the fact that the president
walked away from the summit in Vietnam
is a very positive thing.
I think that that was
the right thing to do.
We don't want a bad deal
that makes us less safe.
- And before I let you go,
the president's going
to roll out a budget,
and there's going to be something in there
that's going to be quite
alarming to some allies.
The president's going to advocate perhaps
wherever we have troops overseas,
think Japan, South Korea, Germany
he's going to ask for cost plus fifty.
Essentially tax countries
over and above where we have bases.
What does that do to the
diplomacy for this country?
- I think it would be
absolutely devastating.
We benefit tremendously.
If you look at the last 70 years,
we have been able to benefit both
from the perspective
of freedom, prosperity,
security, safety because of our bases
and our cooperation with our allies.
The notion that we are somehow
now going to charge them
cost plus fifty, is
really it's wrongheaded
and it would be devastating
to the security of the nation
and our allies.
- Do you think
your Republican Party will support this?
- I won't.
- [Chuck] But the party might.
- Well, I think it's
going to be very important
for us to make sure that people
understand the danger that
that will do to our relationships
and to our fundamental security.
Our security, we've
been able to protect it
because of our alliances
and because we've been able
to work with countries.
And we should not look
at this as though somehow
we need to charge them
rent or for the privilege
of having our forces there
because that does us a
huge benefit as well.
- Congresswoman Liz Cheney,
Republican from Wyoming,
thanks for coming on.
- Thank you, Chuck, good to be with you.
- Good to see you here.
When we come back,
Democrats are going through
the same growing pains
Republicans did when
the Tea Party emerged.
It's hard to keep
competing factions happy.
That and the waiting for Biden campaign.
The panel is next.
(water splashing)
- [Announcer] Guys do whatever it takes
to deal with shave irritation.
So we reimagined the razor with
the new Gillette skin guard.
It has a unique guard between the blades
that's designed to reduce
irritation during the shave.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
Gillette.
- [Announcer] This is Golden
Corral's hand-cut sirloin,
now topped with delicious shrimp scampi.
And here's the premium butterfly shrimp,
and the teriyaki salmon.
Get it all, plus the entire
buffet for one low price.
There's something for
everyone at Golden Corral.
(gentle music)
- [Announcer] In Key West,
you can get close to nature.
Close to history.
And really close to the band.
In fact, Key West is close to perfect,
but far from normal.
- [Reader] If you want to
know why people sacrifice
everything for love you have to start
by asking--
- Could listening to audible
help you find the secret
to a stronger relationship?
- [Reader] Sometimes it
doesn't take anything at all
for us to--
- Just say, Alexa,
give me my free audible book,
and your first pick is on us.
- To the first teacher
who took me seriously.
- To the professor who
pulled me aside and said,
you got this.
- To the pilots who let me in the cockpit,
but didn't let me touch anything.
(robot whirs)
- To Grace Hopper.
- To Mae Jemison.
- To Miss Frizzle.
What?
- To Mrs. Schweinke.
- To my aunt.
(speaking foreign language)
- To whoever comes after me.
- Let me help show you the way.
- [Man] When more girls go into STEM,
the whole world benefits.
- Thank the role model who inspired you.
- Thank you.
(speaking foreign language)
- [Man] Create your own thank you.
- CoQ10 is the number on
cardiologist-recommended
supplement for heart health.
I take Qunol CoQ10.
Why?
Because Qunol has three
times better absorption
than regular CoQ10.
Qunol, the better CoQ10.
- [Announcer] Allergy sufferers,
your senses of smell, hearing,
and taste are being censored.
Dulled by allergy congestion.
Regain your senses with Nasacort.
It's more effective than anti-histamines
on your worst nasal symptoms,
including congestion.
Nasacort, live unsensored.
- When I was playing ball,
they called me The Big Hurt.
But now that I left the game,
Mother Nature started
putting a big hurt on me.
I just couldn't stay in
shape like I used to.
But luckily I found out about Nugenix.
- [Announcer] Nugenix is a
unique man-boosting formula
that helps increase your
free testosterone levels.
- [Frank] Thanks to Nugenix,
I'm really getting after it again.
- [Announcer] Feel stronger, leaner,
with more energy and drive.
- She'll like the difference too.
- [Announcer] To get a
complementary bottle text Flash,
to 369369, that's F-L-A-S-H, to 369369.
- [Announcer] At HomeLight.com
- Welcome back, panel
is here, Pat McCrory,
the former Republican
Governor of North Carolina.
María Teresa Kumar,
President of Voto Latino.
Kasie Hunt, NBC News
Capitol Hill correspondent
and host of Kasie DC on MSNBC.
And Robert Costa,
the moderator of Washington Week on PBS.
Kasie, let's unpack, first, the Hill,
before we get to the presidential race.
Because the Hill debate is going
to animate the presidential race.
Let me play Nancy Pelosi
on Omar, from Friday.
- The incident that happened was,
I don't think our
colleague is anti-Semitic.
I think she has a different
experience in the use of words,
doesn't understand that
some of them are fraught
with meaning that she didn't realize
but, nonetheless, that we had to address.
- I will say this,
Speaker Pelosi has given
me my new favorite excuse.
She has a different experience
in the use of words.
That is easily, now, going to be one of my
favorite new phrases.
This is not easy.
- It's not easy, Chuck.
I think the one thing,
when you speak with,
you know, members of the Democratic Party,
who are frustrated with how
their own party handled this,
there are a lot of Jewish and
non-Jewish Democrats, frankly,
who are upset that this
resolution was as broad as it was.
You know, they'll say,
this is the third time
this has happened.
You know, she said Israel
was hypnotizing the world,
in a tweet before she was in office.
She had that, you know, Benjamins tweet
you showed the audience
at the top of the show.
And now, she had this.
And so you know, every single time,
she has pled ignorance of these tropes.
But you know, they're tropes for a reason.
She's picking up on, you know, language
that is used that is
anti-Semitic, quite frankly.
So you know, I think Nancy Pelosi is doing
what she has very
carefully done since this
new caucus has come together,
which is try to very
carefully thread that needle
and try to sew these two
very disparate generations
together and it's getting harder.
- But there's only so much
Speaker Pelosi can do.
I met with some House
Democrats, seasoned veterans,
over the weekend and late last week.
And they said, in this day
and age of social media,
where someone like Representative Omar
or Representative Ocasio-Cortez
can have millions of followers,
that the old rules don't apply.
And so Speaker Pelosi may try
to cobble together legislation
to send a message to voters.
But the people who have political capital
inside this party are those
with a social media following.
- Okay, if you get off social
media, the world looks normal.
- [Maria] Fairly different.
- But if you live on social
media, I mean, you know,
I don't mean to carry this over.
The NBA is having a problem.
Its players make all this money,
and they're depressed all the time,
because they live on social media
and feel every negative comment
and live it and all of this.
This is what's happening
to this younger generation.
- Exactly right and part of it is, too,
that you actually don't even know
who is really tweeting you.
Are they bots or are they real people,
when it comes to, basically, feeling this?
And I think that the challenge is that
President Trump has really
done a fantastic job
communicating to a broader
audience, based on his tweets.
And it's toe to toe,
now, with a generation
that actually expects
that they're going to have
their breaking news not on the front page
of The New York Times but through a tweet.
And then you don't
actually know how to have
the accurate literacy of,
is this actually accurate?
And that's a challenge.
- As a former mayor and former governor,
I always thought
resolutions without actions
were empty gestures.
And this resolution was an empty gesture
which tried to please everyone
and ended up pleasing no one.
But the problem, for the Democrats,
with these new Millennials, I
call them the AOC Millennials,
is not only do the
Millennials think they have
all the answers they think
they already have wisdom.
And the Nancy Pelosis of
the world have wisdom.
And they're trying to explain
to these younger people,
wait a minute, I'm the old person.
And you cannot make that argument.
- All right.
(group argues)
- Bring it on, there you go.
Bring it on, Kasie.
- I mean, honestly, I think that
the leaders can learn something
from the newer, I take
your point that, you know,
they have not had the kind
of experience in government.
And I think, to a certain extent,
there are going to be consequences
for some of the actions
they take on social media
in, kind of, the universe of
trying to get things done.
But on the other hand,
I think the old guard
doesn't really understand
the power of what they bring.
- By the way, guys, I want
to insert somebody into here,
really quickly.
First of all, the Times
set it up really well.
The Times said, this is the
debate in the Democratic Party,
what you guys are arguing about.
"Do Americans simply pine
for a pre-Trump equilibrium,
"less chaos and more consensus,
"or do the yawning
disparities of these times
call out for a more
transformational administration?"
- [Kasie] And I think
that's absolutely valid.
- Now, listen to AOC yesterday.
- Pat, listen to this.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Moderate is not a stance.
It's just an attitude
toward life of, like, meh.
The meh is, like, worshiped now for what?
- I rest my case.
But the point I want to make
is there's another issue
that brought out the AOC Millennials
against the traditional,
liberal Democrats.
That was Amazon.
Cuomo and one of the most
liberal mayors of New York City
we've ever had gave tax breaks
to a major multibillion-dollar company.
AOC fought it and said, well,
we can spend that $2 billion elsewhere.
Well, the $2 billion didn't exist.
She didn't have the knowledge
necessary of the economy.
Now, philosophy, that's a good argument.
That's also showing the division
in the Democratic Party.
- Right, but I actually
think that what Millennials
are feeling is that they are
feeling from their experience.
They know that something is off.
They know that their experience of,
that they're going to have
a guaranteed brighter future
than their parents is
just not going to happen.
- [Kasie] It's broken.
- It's broken,
and the fact that.
- The compact is broken.
- Absolutely.
- It used to be that if you worked hard,
and you followed the
ethics of your parents,
you would end up working for a company
that would take care
of you for a long time.
That is not the case anymore.
It is simply not the case.
And people resent it.
- It's bigger than age.
I mean the point
Representative Ocasio-Cortez
is making is that the Democratic Party
needs to move to the left.
If you look at this
2020 presidential race,
where is the energy?
Fundraising, Senator Bernie Sanders,
crowds, Senator Bernie Sanders.
He's in his upper 70s.
Yet, he's the runner up from '16.
And he's saying to people like
the representative from New York,
I'm your type of candidate.
I'm not a meh candidate, to use her term.
- The Bernie-Biden, by the way,
it takes two 75-plus-year-old
guys, I guess,
to have this argument,
between this generational argument here.
By the way are they placeholders for now,
until the younger generation
gets more grassroots support?
- Well, I actually think
that everybody's waiting in
the wings, in large part,
because they're waiting
for Beto to announce.
And unlike all of the other Democrats
that are trying to move
as far to the left,
to say, yeah, I am your person,
he has not, necessarily,
said that he is.
And he's much more palatable
to a lot of the independents.
And he's done that in
a very interesting way.
Because again, if you ask
him where his policies are,
they're not on the left.
- He's all things
to all people.
- If there's a criticism,
right, if there's a criticism of Beto,
it's that he doesn't know where he stands
on a lot of things.
- But all these left-wing--
- If you read some of those interviews.
- All these left-wing stances,
the green plan especially,
where the Millennials
are going to realize,
they have to have energy and
power at an affordable price.
They're going to find
out energy is not cheap.
And you need energy to survive.
And the reality's going to wake them up
sometime down the road.
- This is a conversation
that needs more time,
and I might actually give it more time.
But when we come back,
President Trump says
Michael Cohen is lying
about asking for a pardon.
Cohen says it's Mr. Trump who's lying.
All right, so what does Adam Schiff think?
Because Michael Cohen
has lied to him, too.
The chairman of the House
Intelligence Committee
joins me next.
- [Announcer] Think only
specialty stores have what's new?
Olay has the hottest debut.
New Olay clay stick masks.
Hydrating facial mist.
And brightening eye cream.
Only by Olay.
- I was so embarrassed
about paying too much
for a used car, I went into hiding
in this undisclosed location.
- Only carfax.com can give
you the most accurate price
based on the Carfax report.
Stop the shame of overpaying and start
your used car search today at carfax.com.
- Hmm, I'm curious.
- What is it doc?
- Well I'm not quite sure.
But I'd like to prescribe
my proprietary elixir.
- Doctor Turner's Elixir,
as in, you Doctor Turner.
- Yes.
- And you say this stuff works?
- Well it works for me ha ha ha.
- [Announcer] What if doctors were like
most financial advisors?
- You take care.
- Creative Planning is different.
We never sell proprietary products,
in fact, we don't even offer them.
Call for a free, no
obligation consultation.
- I'm a dancer, I live in New York City,
casting directors will send me a video
of choreography and say,
if you can be here in a
couple hours the job is yours.
And then I need my phone to work
while I'm on the subway or
streaming the video they sent me
while I learn the
choreography as best I can.
The key is to hold the bar
up top and not the pole
so that you have full range of motion.
It's a little kooky (laughs).
- [Announcer] There for
you when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network now comes
with Apple Music on us.
Get a free Galaxy S10e when you buy--
(somber music)
- Oh my god I can't believe it!
- Hi mom.
- We said we weren't going
to do this again, remember?
- You get a day.
This time tomorrow you
are back in sober living.
- Yeah, okay.
- You come back and then this happens,
this is on you.
- If you really knew me,
you'd be done with me.
- I do know you.
- [Ben] No you don't.
- You need to come home!
- [Holly] Not without Ben.
- [Announcer] Rated R.
Buy or rent today and
watch anytime, anywhere
on your favorite screens
with DirecTV Cinema.
Movies start at channel 125.
(suspenseful music)
(bugs skittering)
- Termites.
Feasting on homes 24/7.
We're on the move.
- Roger!
(wings fluttering)
(machine whirring)
- Hey Rick, all good?
- Oh yeah, we're good.
We're good.
- [Announcer] Termites
never stop trying to get in,
we never stop working to keep them out.
Terminix, defenders of home.
- [Man] You need this bed.
- Where do you see your party right now?
- It's going to be, how do we
think government should work
and who do we think
government should work for?
- You at the time were
personally opposed to the death penalty,
are you still?
- I've been my entire life,
and I still am.
- Would you commit to choosing a woman
as your vice presidential candidate?
- You know I'll be looking to women first?
- Do you have views on
whether or not US troops
should be in Syria in
any sort of long run?
Does it give you a way to talk to people
who might be much more
conservative than you are
on these issues now?
- Welcome back.
This was a week in which we saw
President Trump's former
campaign chairman Paul Manafort
get sentenced to prison.
Think about that for a moment.
The man who made sure Donald Trump
secured the nomination at
the Republican convention
was sentenced to 47 months in prison,
with sentencing in another
case coming this week.
We also saw Mr. Trump
and Michael Cohen each
call the other a liar over
whether Cohen sought a pardon
from the president.
There's a lot to chew on.
We're going to turn to the chairman
of the House Intelligence
Committee, Adam Schiff,
who joins me now from Los Angeles.
And on spring-forward day,
I'm very grateful for you
getting up that extra hour early.
Congressman Schiff, welcome
back to Meet the Press, sir.
- Thank you.
- Let me just start with
a basic question here.
Who's lying, the president
or Michael Cohen,
when it comes to whether Michael
Cohen asked for a pardon?
And more importantly,
did Michael Cohen lie to Congress again?
- Well, the central question
of our investigation is:
Why did Michael Cohen
lie before our committee
about Moscow Trump Tower?
Why would this be in his interest?
Was this something that he did alone
or were there others involved in it?
And there are reasons to believe
that this was not a lone
decision of Michael Cohen.
What we are looking for
is corroborative evidence.
And the reason why this,
this whole Moscow Trump Tower issue
is so central to our investigation is
that it explains or potentially explains
the president's bizarre
affinity for Vladimir Putin.
And that is that he
stood to make more money
from this transaction
than any deal in his life
and sought the Kremlin's
help to make it happen
while concealing this from the public.
That still may be an animating
principle for the president.
He may believe that when he leaves office
that he still wants to build this tower.
And while that may not be criminal,
it is nonetheless corrupt
and distorts our policy.
So, you know, that is certainly
the central question for us.
In terms of who's telling the truth
between Michael Cohen and the president,
we know that the president has made
probably over a thousand false statements
about the Russia issues.
And here we're going to
simply have to find what
corroboration we can to find
out where the truth lies.
- I was just going to
say is it safe to say
you can't take Michael Cohen
at his word on anything?
- I don't think in terms of
making the case to the public,
and here we're not making
the case to a jury,
about what took place
that we can rely solely
on the testimony of Michael Cohen.
We're going to need corroboration.
You know, to me in looking
at what Michael Cohen
said in the open hearing,
and then what his lawyers said afterwards,
it was very much like
what Donald Trump did
when he said that he had no
knowledge of these payments
to Stormy Daniels and
then Rudy Giuliani said,
oh yes, he did.
Well, where is the truth there?
We asked Michael Cohen
about this extensively.
Those transcripts will be made public.
The public can evaluate
his credibility themselves.
- You know, it looks like,
we don't know this for sure,
but it looks like Robert
Mueller's going to complete his
investigation without
subpoenaing the president
before the grand jury
or coming up with a way
to have him interviewed
before the grand jury.
President Clinton went before
Ken Starr's grand jury.
If indeed Mr. Mueller decides
not to issue that subpoena
or figure out how to get the president
in front of that grand jury,
is that going to have been a mistake
considering we have so many questions
about whose testimony should you believe,
Michael Cohen's or Donald Trump's?
- Yes, I think it is a mistake.
And I've said all along that
I don't think Bob Mueller
should rely on written answers.
When you get written
answers from a witness,
it's really the lawyers' answers
as much as the client's answer.
And here you need to be able
to ask follow-up questions in real time.
But I think the constraint
that Bob Mueller's
operating under is he had
an acting attorney general
who was appointed because
he would be hostile
to a subpoena on the president.
And now he has a
permanent attorney general
who was chosen for the same
hostility to his investigation,
who would likely oppose that step.
I also think that the special counsel
feels some time pressure
to conclude his work.
And knowing that the
White House would drag out
a fight over the subpoena
that may be an issue as well.
But I do think ultimately it's a mistake
because probably the
best way to get the truth
would be to put the president under oath.
Because as he's made plain in the past,
he feels it's perfectly
fine to lie to the public.
After all, he has said,
"It's not like I'm talking
before a magistrate."
Well maybe he should
talk before a magistrate.
- I want to move to something
that was a bit confusing.
Erik Prince, who is the brother of
the secretary of education
but also has been
sort of before your committee having to do
with some odd meetings that he
had set up in the Seychelles,
he was on Al Jazeera and he
was asked about some testimony
to your committee and about
whether he lied or not.
Take a listen.
- We were there to talk about Iran policy.
- You were there to
talk about Iran policy?
- Uh-huh.
- Don't you think that's
something important
to disclose to the House
Intelligence Committee
while you're under oath?
- I did.
- You didn't, we just went
through the testimony.
(audience laughing)
There's no mention of the Trump
Tower meeting August 2016.
Why not?
- I don't know if they
got the transcript wrong.
- So this was about another meeting
that Erik Prince had I
believe with some other,
perhaps with some other representatives
of some other countries in Trump Tower,
the so-called second Trump Tower meeting
of less significance.
Not with Russians, with
other foreign countries.
Based on what you heard there,
is Mr. Prince telling the truth?
Is your transcript wrong?
- Well, he's certainly
not telling the truth
in that interview.
There's nothing wrong with our transcript.
There was nothing wrong with the reporter
who transcribed his testimony.
He did not disclose that
meeting to our committee.
And in fact, as you can see
from the published
transcript of his interview,
he was asked what kind of
role he played, if any,
in the campaign, and
he said he had no role
apart from on his own
submitting written papers,
hanging a yard sign, or
making a contribution.
And he was also asked about
any substantive policy conversations
that he might have had.
So his, you know,
interview certainly looks
inconsistent with his testimony.
Bob Mueller has that testimony already.
And Bob Mueller will
have to make the decision
about whether that rises to a
level of deliberate falsehood.
But we had questions at
the time of his testimony
about his candor and his,
how forthcoming he was and those questions
have only been heightened now.
- What's your concern
about what he was doing?
- Well, the concern is that, you know,
this is another concealed meeting.
This is another discussion that took place
in the context of the meeting
that he had in the Seychelles.
There have been persistent questions
about whether the U.A.E. was
playing a back channel role
to the Russians during the campaign.
And those were a lot of the questions
that we were asking him about.
So clearly this meeting at
Trump Tower with these players
was of direct interest to our committee.
So why conceal it?
Why withhold that information
if there was nothing improper,
no improper purpose in it?
There are a lot of deeply concerning
and unanswered questions
around Erik Prince
and his involvement with the campaign.
- All right, Adam Schiff,
I will leave it there.
The Democratic lead on the
House Intelligence Committee,
the chairman.
Thanks very much for coming
on, getting up early,
and sharing your views
with us this morning.
- Thank you.
- When we come back,
the state the Democrats
have on their minds for 2020.
Could it be the game changer
that gets them over 270?
- [Woman] Another month?
- There are procedures and they will come.
- Oh is that what I tell the investors.
- Tell them we don't have to do this
one country at a time.
BDO says the approval process is similar
throughout Latin America.
- So parallel tracks?
- If we have first-hand
experience in each country.
- And BDO can find these people?
- BDO has these people.
- [Announcer] People who know,
know BDO.
- Today we pancake together,
to make the 12th of March
IHOP Free Pancake Day.
- [Group] Pancakes!
- Hey!
What I tell you bozos about
playing in the exhibits?
- To not?
- Come into IHOP Free Pancake
Day on Tuesday March 12th.
- [Announcer] If you live with diabetes,
why finger stick when you can scan.
With the FreeStyle Libre 14-day system,
just scan the sensor with
your reader or iPhone,
and manage your diabetes.
With the FreeStyle Libre 14-day system,
a continuous glucose monitor,
you can check your glucose levels anytime
without finger sticks.
Ask your doctor to write a prescription
for the new FreeStyle Libre 14-day system.
You can do it without finger sticks.
Learn more at freestylelibre.us.
(upbeat tone)
- [Announcer] From two stories to 20,
from ready apps to emergency response,
whenever damage strikes
call on the cleanup team
that's fast to any size disaster
at 1-800-SERVPRO, like
it never even happened.
(adventurous rock music)
- [Announcer] We humans
are strange creatures.
Other species avoid pain and struggle.
We actually seek it out.
Other species do difficult
things because they have to.
We do difficult things
because we like to.
We think it's fun.
Introducing the all new 2019 Ford Ranger.
Built for the strangest of all creatures.
- Russia, if you're listening--
- [Announcer] The Mueller
report might not be ready,
but ours is.
From the infamous meeting.
- The question is what did Trump know,
and what did Trump direct?
- [Announcer] To the secret talks.
- I think Donald Trump is being handled
like he would be handled if Vladimir Putin
was still a KGB officer.
- [Announcer] What we know
about Trump and Putin.
- Again and again,
what happens in this
particular investigation,
are ties to Russia.
- [Announcer] Russia, if you're listening,
Trump & Putin at nine,
followed by Headliners
Robert Mueller at 10,
tonight on MSNBC.
(orchestral music)
You're watching MSNBC.
- I wanna offer some
advice to you the viewer
as we enter the presidential campaign.
What should count most
for us doing the covering
and for you out there making the decisions
about who to support and
vote for ultimately is.
Who will they fight for?
What will they fight for?
Can they be trusted to do what they say?
Everything else is noise.
And trust me,
there will be an awful lot of
noise in the next 22 months.
We're committed to try
to turn down the din
and get answers about what matters.
(upbeat electronic music)
- Welcome back, Data Download time.
Heading into the 2020 election,
Democrats are excited
about the opportunity
for an electoral pickup.
It's not Texas, it's not Arizona,
but Georgia.
That's right, a state that hasn't voted
for a Democrat for president
since Bill Clinton in 1992.
Let's look to Cobb County.
It's a suburb of Atlanta, part of which,
Newt Gingrich represented,
and the rapidly changing
politics of the last few years.
In 2012, Cobb County voted
for Republican Mitt Romney
for president by a whopping 12 points.
Just four years later, it
swung to Hillary Clinton,
and she won the county by just two points.
And before you say, oh, that's
just a Donald Trump anomaly,
realize that this past
November, Stacey Abrams,
the Democratic candidate for governor,
won Cobb County by nearly 10 points,
so a 22-point swing in just six years.
What's going on?
We went down to Cobb
County to figure it out.
- Yeah it's changing out in Cobb County.
Lots of people were Republicans,
and now we've had a lot of move-ins,
and it's getting a mixture now.
Like Georgia's becoming a mixture.
You know, I sort of liked it when,
you know, the Republican part of it.
- It's true, Cobb County
has seen a ton of people
move in the last few years.
Between 2010 and 2017,
Cobb County's population grew 9.8 percent,
outpacing growth in Georgia, as a whole.
In that same time, Cobb
County has grown more diverse,
with increases to both
the African American
and Hispanic populations.
More residents also have college degrees.
And median household income has gone
from $66000 to $72000 per year.
The more telling data may be
where the transplants to
Cobb County are coming from.
Of the top 20 counties that
people move to Cobb from,
since 2012, 13 are from
outside the state of Georgia.
And 15 of those counties
voted for Hillary Clinton,
including Queens, New York,
LA County, and Miami-Dade.
This is just Cobb County, of course.
But you can see a lot of these changes
in the other suburban counties,
where the vote has also
swung towards the Democrats
in and around Atlanta.
So is Georgia ready to
be a swing state again?
- The younger crowd is definitely
going to go toward this.
- I have no doubt that
a progressive candidate
could win statewide.
- I think Georgia's been
a swing state before.
I think it's moving
towards that way again.
- I just can't imagine
not being a red state,
I really can't.
- We'll find out soon enough.
Coming up, Paul Manafort,
a controversial sentence,
and that claim that he's lived
an otherwise blameless life.
(tea kettle whistles)
- [Announcer] This is your wakeup call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis,
month after month the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
Humira can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
Humira targets and blocks
the source of inflammation
that contributes to joint
pain and irreversible damage.
- [Announcer] Humira
can lower your ability
to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes fatal infections
including tuberculosis and
cancers including lymphoma
have happened, as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening heart failure.
Tell your doctor if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB, Hepatitis B,
are prone to infections or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start Humira if
you have an infection.
- [Announcer] Help stop the clock
on further irreversible joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here, right now, Humira.
- Discover?
- Hi what's the Social Security alert?
- It's a free alert if we find
your Social Security number
on the Dark Web.
- Good because I was a little worried
about my information getting out.
- [Customer Service Rep] Why's that?
- My social is 875 dash six.
- Okay, I see.
(parrot laughs)
- Somebody thinks it's hilarious.
- Free Social Security
alerts from Discover.
- [Announcer] This is Golden
Corral's hand-cut sirloin,
now topped with delicious shrimp scampi.
And here's the premium butterfly shrimp,
and the teriyaki salmon.
Get it all, plus the entire
buffet, for one low price.
- Ahh it's just what I thought.
It's all going to have to come out.
(woman breathes sharply)
- Ooh.
(country music)
- If you don't have dental insurance,
paying the bill can be really expensive.
After all just a simple
cleaning can cost $150.
And other procedures like
crowns and root canals
can cost hundreds, even thousands more.
But now you can get dental insurance
for about a dollar a day,
from Physicians Mutual Insurance Company.
Call us for a free information kit.
Our dental insurance helps
cover over 350 procedures.
Everything from cleanings and fillings
to crowns and dentures.
Your acceptance is guaranteed for one of
these insurance policies,
even if you're retired,
or on Medicare, there are no deductibles,
and there's no annual maximum.
Plus you can see any dentist you choose.
Take the pain out of big dental bills
with Physicians Mutual.
Call us now for your free information kit
with all the details.
- Back now with End Game.
When the Des Moines Register found out
we were leading with
the Democratic divide,
they, of course, decided,
oh, we should hurry up
and get our poll in the field.
I don't think that was
the order of events.
But let me put up the
Des Moines Register poll
that's out this morning because it's going
to have everybody talking.
And it's both meaningful and meaningless
all at the same time.
We see who the top two candidates
are, Biden and Sanders.
Only ones in double digits.
Warren at nine, Harris at seven,
and in case you're wondering,
right below Harris is Beto, at five,
Booker and Klobuchar the
only other two over 1%.
What is interesting there, Robert Costa,
is the fact that you can
tell that buzz is everything.
Bernie's numbers went up six points
from the last time it went down.
And what's the difference
between last time and this time?
Bernie's in the middle
of an announcement tour.
So these things will continue to move
as announcement tours happen.
- And Senator Sanders, if you
watch him closely right now,
he's running as a movement politician.
He's gotten rid of his
traditional consultants,
like Tad Devine.
He has built a movement
from his 2016 campaign.
And you look at Senator
Warren, she has a message.
Break up the big companies, go after tech.
But it's a crowded space
on that left side of the Democratic Party.
- You know, Chuck, one of
the most interesting things,
I think, is in that poll is that,
if you look at the numbers for Biden,
the biggest chunk of them,
if you ask who their second choice is,
the answer's Bernie Sanders,
which is pretty remarkable.
And, you know, I do think--
- I thought so, too, it shows you
they're the mainstream of the party,
the two of them together.
- Potentially, yes.
And frankly, Bernie
Sanders' fundraising means
that he is going to be a factor.
I mean, he has a core
of supporters, you know?
I'm not sure it's big enough
to win him any big states.
But if he pulls, you know,
20%, 25% consistently,
he's going to have the
money to go the distance.
Mark my words, you're going
to see him at the convention.
- And Bernie Sanders is
one of the few people
who never stopped campaigning.
He does Facebook Lives,
where he has 35000 people,
just on the spot, watching
him and following him.
And what folks don't realize
is that he really appeals
to a lot of young voters.
For the very first time, young
voters are going to outweigh,
potentially, the Millennials,
excuse me, the Baby Boomers.
For the very first time,
they're going to actually have
more eligible voters than we've ever seen.
- Well, therefore, I'd like to apologize
and do a resolution.
- Are you running?
- Based upon what I said
about the Millennials.
But I would like to say this.
The more these candidates get out,
we're going to see Trump numbers go up.
Because there is going to be a comparison
and it's already happening.
And I think, also, the
more Congressman Schiff
talks about investigations
and continuing these investigations
after the Mueller report, I
think Trump numbers will go up.
I think the Democrats are
going to put Trump in office.
- Speaking of the
president, I want to play
what he said about Paul Manafort.
Because there's a part of the empathy
that I really don't get,
when it comes to being
the sitting president
of the United States.
Take a listen.
- I feel very badly for Paul Manafort.
I think it's been a very,
very tough time for him.
But if you notice, both his lawyer,
a highly respected man, and a
very highly respected judge,
the judge said there was
no collusion with Russia.
- Well, the judge did not say that,
though the judge did
say this about Manafort,
"I think the sentencing
range is excessive.
"Manafort has been a
good friend to others,
"a generous person.
"He has lived an
otherwise blameless life."
What I don't understand Robert Costa,
is why the president is
praising and feeling sorry
for a man that defrauded
American taxpayers
for at least $6 million.
- And you know who else wonders that?
Many Trump advisors.
Talking to them, in recent
days, they wish the president
would actually be quiet
about Paul Manafort.
They wish Judge Ellis, of Alexandria,
would be their spokesman.
- [Chuck] Could've been.
- Because they say he's the
person who's actually making
the best case for this administration.
Bill Shine, the deputy chief of staff,
out as the communications head,
the president going on and on,
talking about possible pardons.
They wish all that would just be noise.
It's the Ellis case,
diminishing the Mueller probe,
that's what the White House really wants.
But they can't stay on message.
- [Chuck] Because of Manafort.
- There's a video right
now, a famous video,
of a whale almost swallowing
a person swimming in the
ocean and he spits him out.
Trump needs to spit Manafort out.
And the chairman of the
Intelligence Committee
needs to get rid of Cohen.
Stay away from both of them.
They're not good for either party.
- I think, first, we need to clarify
that this what he was
getting sentenced for
was not for Russian collusion.
So that we have to set the table for--
- No, but he was ripping
off the American government
over 30 years of lobbying.
- Exactly right.
Exactly right and so
one of the conversations
that people are having is that
how unjust the sentence was
for this type of crime.
And we can look at other judges.
But if we look,
particularly, at this judge,
this judge threw the book
at Representative Jefferson,
from Louisiana.
- William Jefferson.
An African American
Democrat from New Orleans.
- Right, who basically said,
who basically was found to have
embezzled close to $400000.
- The freezer cash, the
infamous freezer cash.
- Those numbers are so much lower
than what Paul Manafort was dealing with.
- Well, and this is where you talk about,
is there justice, when it
comes to white-collar crime?
Manafort is incredibly connected.
He was basically verging,
teetering, on treason,
when it comes to this.
Was that fair, and that is
where we actually have to unpack
the sentence that he's serving.
- There's more sentencing,
there is more sentencing
coming for Mr. Manafort.
The Spinal Tap drummer
position of the White House,
I mean,
(group laughs)
the communications director
position at the White House.
- [Pat] Wow, that's an
inside joke, I love it.
- I mean, you brought up Bill Shine.
Who will take it?
- Would you want to be the
White House communications
director, Chuck?
- The president is now
the communications director again.
What does this mean, Kasie?
- Well, I think it means, you
know, to Bob's earlier point,
that we're going to see more of the same.
I mean, you know, I
certainly wouldn't want to be
the person that needs to tell
the president of the United States
how to communicate with
the American people.
I mean, good luck.
He's been doing it himself,
literally, his entire life.
- How much did the New Yorker piece
have to do with Shine's quick release?
- The president was
frustrated with Bill Shine
not bringing all of the Fox News expertise
and helping to elevate
his image with the press.
The most revealing speech
of the most recent weeks,
President Trump at CPAC.
- [Chuck] Oh, yeah.
- Two hours.
- [Chuck] Yeah, unpack that.
- [Pat] The volume was at
11 for President Trump,
during that speech.
- Ah that's all I have for today.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for springing forward with us.
We'll be back next week.
Because if it's Sunday,
no matter the hour,
it's Meet the Press.
- [Announcer] More
Americans watch NBC News
than any other news
organization in the world.
- I've always been amazed by what's next,
and still going for my best,
even though I live with
a higher risk of stroke
due to AFIB not caused
by a heart valve problem.
So if there's a better
treatment than Warfarin,
I want that too.
Eliquis.
Eliquis is proven to reduce stroke risk
better than Warfarin, plus,
at significantly less major
bleeding than Warfarin.
Eliquis is FDA-approved and has both.
What's next, reeling in a nice one.
- [Announcer] Don't stop taking Eliquis
unless your doctor tells you to,
as stopping increases your
risk of having a stroke.
Eliquis can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take Eliquis if you have
an artificial heart valve,
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking Eliquis you
may bruise more easily.
And it may take longer than usual
for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden signs of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
Eliquis may increase your bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor about all planned
medical or dental procedures.
- [Man] Eliquis, the number one
cardiologist prescribed blood thinner.
Ask your doctor if Eliquis
is what's next for you.
(water splashes)
- [Announcer] Guys do whatever it takes
to deal with shave irritation.
So we re-imagined the razor
with the new Gillette skin guard.
It has a unique guard between the blades
that's designed to reduce
irritation during a shave.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
Gillette.
- I don't keep track of regrets
and I don't add up the years,
but what I do count on is Boost.
- [Announcer] Delicious Boost
High Protein nutritional drink
has 20 grams of protein along with
26 essential vitamins and minerals.
Boost High Protein.