- Honoring the very best of us.
And that does it for this edition
of Andrea Mitchell Reports.
Here's Ali Velshi from Stephanie Ruhle.
- Andrea, have yourself a
great afternoon, thank you.
And hello everyone, it's
Wednesday, July 3rd.
Coming up this hour on Velshi and Ruhle
the crisis at the border.
We've got new gut-wrenching
details about how children
are being are being treated in US custody.
It would be considered abuse
if it happened in a home.
So should immigration
officials be held to account?
Plus, President Trump says he's cutting
prescription drug prices.
For facts sake, thousands of
drug prices are skyrocketing.
We're gonna dig into the numbers for you.
And military tanks have
arrived on the national mall
for President Trump's
July 4th celebration.
We'll look at the cost, plus
concerns from the Pentagon.
Today President Trump is insisting
that his fight for adding
a citizenship question
to the census isn't over
yet, saying in a tweet quote,
"The news reports about
the Department of Commerce
"dropping it's quest to put
the citizenship question
"on the census is incorrect or,
"to state it differently, fake!
"We are absolutely moving
forward, as we must,
"because of the importance of
the answer to this question."
Now the statement, refuting his
very own commerce secretary,
Wilbur Ross who said, just 24
hours ago, this in part quote,
"The Census Bureau has started the process
"of printing the decennial questionnaires
"without the question.
"My focus, and that of the
Bureau and the entire Department
"is to conduct a complete
and accurate census."
All of this of course,
follows the Supreme Court
recent decision to block the
question from the 2020 Census.
Joining me now NBC's
White House correspondent,
Kelly O'Donnell.
Kelly, this one's a tricky one,
because while the president
often tweets things
that are at odds wit his administration
or his own government.
The Commerce Department
actually has to print the census
and the census actually has to go out.
This one seems to be easy to identify,
what the story actually is.
Why are the president and
the Commerce Department
not on the same page
about this, literally?
- Well, you could argue there
are two different tracks.
There's the practical piece
of having to print the census
with, in this case, no
question about citizenship
for those who participate,
because 2020 is knocking on our door,
in terms of the volume of
what it takes to do a census.
And in Wilbur Ross, the
secretary's own name,
you read the statement.
This is very clearly coming
from the Department of Commerce.
We also heard from Justice
Department officials,
who told us that it was going
forward with the printing.
So, where is the second level?
You could continue the legal challenge
and make it an issue
that could be resolved
at some later date or, arguably,
you could say you could
reprint portions of the census
or it could be for the next census.
It's unclear, the president
doesn't lay that out.
So, it appears to be
more political messaging
that the president,
who has taken a very
strong position on this.
Just Monday, he was
asked about this question
in the Oval Office.
Would he attempt to delay the census,
which is required by the Constitution.
Not an everyday law,
the Constitution that it
be done every 10 years.
He said he was strongly looking at that.
So, the president wanting
to stick with that position,
but leaving, as he explained
in the Oval on Monday,
that this is a question
he believes is appropriate
and that it is the
country's right to know who,
among those participating,
is a citizen, who is not.
He didn't leave open the
possibility for non-citizens
who have permanent legal
status in the United States,
or those under protected
status, like asylum seekers,
he just had the either/or.
So, it would appear that
the government is doing
what the government needs
to do to begin that process
of the every 10 year check on
who and how many are among us.
And the president is still saying
he wants to fight this fight.
It may be part of his political argument.
It ties into so much else
of the president's rhetoric.
But there's a way for both to be true.
But what we have not yet
heard from the White House,
and we've inquired, is does
the president have a difference
on the actual printing part of this.
It would appear that ship is about to sail
from one of his closest
advisors, Wilbur Ross,
saying, it's gonna happen.
Ali.
- Kelly, good to see you as always.
Thank you Kelly O'Donnell
for us at the White House.
President Trump is celebrating
the acquittal of a Navy Seal
accused of murdering an ISIS fighter.
Just a short time ago
the president tweeted,
"Congratulations to Navy
Seal Eddie Gallagher,
"his wonderful wife Andrea,
and his entire family.
"You have been through much together.
"Glad I could help!"
It's an interesting last line,
"Glad I could help."
This was a trial, how
did the president help?
Gallagher was accused of stabbing to death
a young, wounded ISIS fighter in 2017.
Then posing for a picture with the corpse.
While Gallagher was found not guilty
on six criminal charges,
he was found guilt of posing
for a photo with a casualty.
It was a trial with a stunning twist.
Another Navy Seal testified
that he was the one who killed the boy
by blocking his breathing
tube in an act of mercy.
Joining me now from San Diego,
NBC's Steve Patterson's been covering
the trial from the beginning.
Steve, what help is the
president talking about
in that tweet?
- So, the president isn't
necessarily referring
to the trial itself.
He's referring to an act
that occurred in the past.
There was about a nine-month period
after Gallagher was
arrested on these very,
extremely serious charges for war crimes
over in a 2017 tour of
duty, as you mentioned,
in Mosul, in Iraq,
where he was taken to a military brig.
Again, arrested in the fall,
I believe at his residence.
Taken to the brig and confined there
for a period of nearly a
year, about nine months.
The president takes credit for moving him
out of the brig and back home,
saying that the brig is only for people
that were flight risks
or that have significant
risk of harming someone
or themselves or, obviously,
leaving the country.
His argument was that
Gallagher was at risk
of doing none of that.
He, of course, referenced this,
as he does with most
everything, in a tweet.
Saying quote, "In honor of his
past service to our country,
"Navy Seal Eddie Gallagher
will soon be moved to
"a less restrictive confinement
"while he awaits his day in court.
"Process should move quickly."
It did move quickly.
That was March, he was back
home shortly after that.
We spoke to members of
Gallagher's defense team
on their way into court this morning.
They were praising,
thanking President Trump
for doing this saying that it allowed them
to prepare a significant case,
that they were obviously
able to be successful
in so many of the charges here.
Saying that it was thanks to the president
that he allowed all this press to usher in
because of his exposure to the case.
So they're very happy
with the attention that
the president has given this case.
And, obviously, for whatever
he did to move Gallagher
from confinement to home
so they could prepare
for the trial that we
just experienced, Ali.
- All right Steve.
Thanks very much, Steve
Patterson for us in Los Angeles.
All right, now to the
race for the White House.
Today, several Democratic
candidates are campaigning
in the key voter state of Iowa.
Former Vice President Joe
Biden's campaign just announced
it raised 21-1/2 million dollars
during it's second quarter alone.
This as Senator Kamala Harris
appears to be closing the gap
on Biden's lead days
after she challenged him
on his record with race issues
during the Democratic debate.
A new Quinnipiac University poll shows
Harris is up 13 points
in the last three weeks,
while front-runner Biden
is down eight points.
Harris stands at 20%, Biden at 22,
which is a virtual tie when you consider
the margin of error.
Senator Elizabeth Warren
and Bernie Sanders follow.
But according to the poll,
when voters were asked
who has the best chance
of winning against President Trump,
Biden maintains a strong
42%, Harris is at 14%.
In another poll from The
Washington Post and ABC News,
the biggest jump again
belongs to Senator Harris.
In that poll though,
Senator Bernie Sanders
holds on to second place.
Joining me now from
Iowas, our road warriors:
Vaughn Hillyard, Shaquille
Brewster and Mike Memoli.
Mike, you're following
Joe Biden in Iowa today,
let's talk about the
second quarter for him
in terms of fundraising compared to
the other candidates we know so far.
- Yeah Ali, well we saw last week
the downsides of being the front runner.
In that debate, Joe Biden
put on the defensive
by some of his opponents.
And so, as he arrives today in Iowa
for his first real campaign
rally since the debate,
a little bit of a show of
force from the Biden campaign,
announcing that second-quarter
fundraising number:
$21.5 million dollars
since he entered the race
in late April.
I should mention, it's not as
much as Mayor Pete Buttigeig,
who reported raising more than 25 million.
Bernie Sanders also with
a number of 18 million.
But that's more on a per-day basis,
the Biden campaign points out,
noting that he didn't get
in until three weeks into,
after the fundraising quarter began.
I'll read a few of the
statistics highlighted
by the Biden campaign.
Of course, NBC News has
been keeping a close track
of those high-dollar fundraisers.
27 that he's done since announcing.
That brings in big numbers in a hurry.
But the Biden campaign saying that 97%
of all the donations they've received
are from grass-roots donors.
Those are in amounts of
less than $200 or less.
They also have more than 256,000 donors
who gave a total of 436,000 donations.
So obviously Ali, as Biden's
a little bit on the defensive,
having to deal with that
tense debate exchange
with Kamala Harris.
A little bit of a reminder of the fact
that he's not going anywhere.
And a reminder from the
Biden campaign, as well,
that his dollars
potentially go a lot longer
than a Mayor Pete's, for instance,
because he's got nearly universal name ID.
He doesn't need to spend
that money on TV ads
establishing who he is to voters.
He can invest that all
in their grass roots
and their infrastructure for
their campaign going forward.
- Mike, thank you.
Vaughn Hillyard, Senator Harris is closing
the gap on Biden nationally.
You're covering a Kamala
Harris event in Iowa today.
A new USAToday/Suffolk University poll
shows Biden continues to lead with 24%,
Harris in second place at 16%.
What's her plan to close the
gap and keep the momentum?
It's an important question,
because Kamala Harris
tends to have moments
and she's got to fill up the
space between those moments
to keep that momentum going.
- Yeah, you fill in the
space by campaigning.
She's here in Des Moines.
She'll be appearing over
here in West Des Moines
at this park behind us
here in just about an hour,
before she heads over to the
western part of the state.
She'll hit the TV market
in Council Bluffs,
the Omaha area there.
On Friday, she'll then hit the
Sioux City television market.
The Kamala Harris campaign
said that they plan
to hit the ground running and not let up.
She was over in California
holding fundraisers.
In those first three
days after the debate,
they raised three-and-a
half million dollars,
the campaign said.
The have not released
their quarter totals,
but it should be noted,
she jumped in before anybody
else in this campaign,
raising $12,000,000 in that first quarter,
giving her a leg up here compared
to Mayor Pete Buttigeig and Joe Biden,
who jumped into this race later on.
But for this campaign,
this is about painting
contrasts at this point.
Kamala Harris showed that she was willing
to draw contrasts between herself
and other Democratic candidates,
particularly taking on Joe Biden on
the issue of race, busing,
on the Obama Administration's
deportation policy at the debate.
And now the question is going forward,
to what extent will she
continue to press the case,
essentially prosecute the case
against her fellow Democrats.
And that starts here
on the campaign trail.
She's got two events
today before heading on
across Iowa the next two days.
She'll be in New Orleans then on Saturday
before going to South
Carolina on Sunday and Monday.
Ali.
- All right.
And Shaquille, according to
the Quinnipiac University poll,
Sanders is now in fourth place.
You spoke with the campaign's
senior advisor earlier.
What is the Sanders' campaign
doing to boost momentum
and what's going on in Iowa?
- Well, the say it's not
affecting their strategy
and that's why we have Senator Sanders
about to open up this field
office here in Iowa City.
It's just an example of
how the campaign wants
to focus on what they call "ground game,"
rather than that recent polling.
And I spoke with Senator
Sanders' chief of staff
about that recent polling.
A flood of polls since
our debate last weekend.
As we point out these polls,
he's able to point out several more
that show Sanders closing the
gap with Vice President Biden,
but also polls that show
him ticking up a little bit.
And that's why you have
Senator Sanders, on this trip,
going and participating in
these retail politics events.
So, instead of those big
rallies that we normally see,
he's doing ice cream socials.
He's gonna be marching in
Fourth of July parades.
Really trying to have those
interactions with voters.
And this is a campaign in Iowa
that has scaled up recently.
So right now they have about 43 staffers,
but the campaign notes that is lower
than some of the other
campaigns out there.
They highlight their 25,000 volunteers,
who these staffers are
gonna be able to mobilize.
Folks who are gonna knock
on doors, make calls.
That's why events like
these are happening.
He's gonna be opening up three
offices throughout the state,
and these are recruiting
events, essentially.
Hoping that they can pull in volunteers.
Pull in people to support him
come that caucus in February.
- Shaquille Brewster, Mike
Memoli, Vaughn Hillyard,
thanks to the three of you,
our road warriors on the campaign trail.
We're learning more this week
about the Trump Administration's
immigration policies,
which many critics say
crosses lines of ethics,
human rights, and basic decency.
Next, we'll break down the hellish details
from inside the detention facilties
that come straight from
the government itself.
You're watching Velshi
& Ruhle live on MSNBC.
- Fact is, every insurance
company hopes you drive safely.
But Allstate actually
helps you drive safely.
With Drivewise.
It lets you know when you go too fast
(tires squealing)
and brake too hard.
With feedback to help you drive safer.
Giving you the power to
actually lower your cost.
Unfortunately, it can't
do anything about that.
Now that you know the truth,
(car honking)
are you in good hands?
- [Announcer] Let's get down to business.
The business of family time.
And down time.
And you time.
And forgetting what
time it is all together.
Modernized Comfort Inns &
Suites have been refreshed.
Because when your business is making time,
our business is you.
Get the lowest price
guaranteed on all Choice hotels
when you book direct at choicehotels.com.
- I switched to Miralax
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives forcefully stimulate
the nerves in your colon.
Miralax works with the water in your body
to unblock your system naturally.
And it doesn't cause bloating, cramping,
gas, or a sudden urgency.
Miralax, look for the pink cap.
- The only thing we
love more than slinging.
- Is showing folks how easy it is.
- Explore all the possibilities.
- Your first time slinging
is always so special.
- I cried my first time.
- [Announcer] Get live TV,
only 15 bucks your first month
at slingtv.com.
- Going to the Shawn
Mendes Verizon Up concert
was like an out-of-body experience.
- [Announcer] Why the Yousafzai
sisters chose Verizon.
- We right in front of him.
- Dead center, front row.
Actually Zermina, you
touched Shawn Mendes.
She touched Shawn Mendes.
- Yeah, I touched him.
He, like, held my hand for a while.
And then we got to meet him after,
which was like--
- Another surprise.
- Yeah.
We love Verizon even more now.
I'll never forget that day, ever.
(laughter)
- [Announcer] The network
more people rely on
gives you more.
Like thousands of tickets to concerts,
festivals and private shows.
And big savings on our
best phones when you--
- You're turning onto the street,
when you barely clip a passing car.
Minor accident, no big deal, right?
Wrong.
Your insurance company
is gonna raise your rates
after the other car got a scratch so small
you could have fixed it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that pen
and use it to sign up with a
different insurance company.
- [Announcer] For drivers
with accident forgiveness,
Liberty Mutual won't raise their rates
because of their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty, Liberty, Liberty, Liberty ♪
- [Announcer] This summer,
all eyes will be on the
US Women's National Team.
In the FIFA Women's World Cup.
Over 153 hours of coverage.
Live from France.
The 2019 FIFA Women's World
Cup on Fox, FS1 and FS2.
Don't miss all 52 matches of
the FIFA Women's World Cup,
live in stunning 4K on DirectTV.
If you don't have 4K, ask for it today.
- [Woman] For a free case review.
- Isn't this a situation of
hate the game not the player?
- This is a power play.
This is a strategic move from her, right?
- Why is this potentially such a big deal?
- We have more breaking news.
why wouldn't we?
It's Tuesday in Washington.
- The wall is the sticking
point, not border security.
- Although the promise was
a wall paid for by Mexico.
- I cannot wait to keep
talking about 2020.
I gotta tell you, I
think it's fascinating.
- Your entire business is profiting off
of other people's information,
then your job is to keep
that information safe.
This week we are getting
a better understanding
of the conditions inside detention centers
run by Customs and Border Protection.
And the descriptions give a stark look
at how many desperate
people fleeing violence
and economic uncertainty
at home are treated.
The Department of Homeland Security's
Office of the Inspector General touted
five border facilities
and two ports of entry
in the Rio Grande Valley
and released blunt findings.
According to the report,
about 3,400 detainees were
held longer than 72 hours.
That's the CBP guidelines
for maximum holding time.
In fact, 1,500 of them were
held for more than 10 days.
And it found 826 children
were held longer than
that 72 hour limit.
That represents about 31% of the children
who are held in Customs
and Border Patrol custody.
Despite Customs and Border
Control requirements,
that reasonable efforts to allow detainees
to shower within 72 hours be made,
the report found that
some adults were unable
to shower for up to a month.
Detainees were given
wet-wipes for personal hygiene
and many only got bologna sandwiches,
leading to cases of constipation.
Requirements that
children receive hot meals
were also not being met.
It found that detainees were held
in overcrowded cells for up to a month.
One senior manager described the situation
as a "ticking time bomb."
Democratic lawmakers visited
the detention facilities
this week and many,
including New York congresswoman
Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez,
took to Twitter and interviews
to report on conditions.
They described being told things like
women were told that they
could drink out of the toilets.
They reported migrants being woken
at odd hours for no reason
and being subjected to
disparaging language.
They described it as
psychological warfare.
And a temporary restraining order filed
by a human rights group quoted
several children interviewed
as saying things like,
"we're in a metal cage,"
"it's very cold," "lights
are on all the time,"
"I'm so hungry," "we got sick,"
"I've never been offered a shower."
NBC's Gabe Gutierrez
talked to a pediatrician
who treated some of the
children previously held
in CBP detention.
Here's what she had to say.
- Children should not be in a place
where they don't have access
to their basic human needs.
Where they don't have
access to, if they are sick,
a medical provider.
It is detrimental, not
only to their acute state,
to what's happening right now,
but to their future development
and their mental health.
- All right, joining me
now MSNBC correspondent
Jacob Soboroff.
Jacob, the acting Secretary
of Homeland Security
is calling for an investigation.
However, it's not into the
conditions that I just laid out,
that were in the Office of the
Inspector General's report,
it was something else.
- Yeah, that's right.
He's calling on the Office of
Professional Responsibility,
Ali, within DHS to investigate
what they normally investigate,
which is misconduct,
a lack of standards inside
the department being upheld.
And the results of that
investigation, as you said,
will be specifically about
these Facebook messages
that have been uncovered by Propublica
and what really was
extraordinarily shocking
and dehumanizing language
that was being used
by the folks that were inside this group.
And it's a group of, a
large amount of people.
I think 9,500 people.
But ultimately, it might
come down to the acts
and the language used by
these specific agents,
if indeed they were acting,
current border patrol agents
at the time they used those messages.
- All right.
The ACLU, Jacob, has
just won a legal battle
over asylum seekers.
Can you tell us more about that
and what it means for
the people at the border
and in these detention facilities?
- Yeah, It's extraordinarily
important, as a matter of fact,
because Attorney General Barr
wanted to hold asylum seekers
in custody without any ability
to bond themselves out.
To get out by paying a bail or a bond.
And, frankly, just hold them in detention
for the pendancy of their asylum hearings
and their immigration court hearings.
It's another attempt to deter
migration to this country
by saying if you come here,
try to declare asylum,
we're gonna lock you up, basically.
But at the end of the day,
we're talking about asylum,
we're not talking about criminals.
And the judge seems to have sided,
the judge clearly sided
against Attorney General Barr
here in that case,
and the administration will
not be able to lock people up
who are here only because
they want to seek asylum.
- All right.
The Washington Post, Jacob,
is reporting about a child
who died in May after spending time
in Customs and Border Patrol custody.
What do we know about
this from the autopsy?
- Again, it's a familiar refrain, Ali.
Ultimately this child
died of, the autopsy says,
several diseases, parasites, influenza,
and what the lawyer for
the family is alleging,
now that this autopsy is out,
is that this child should
have gotten treatment
far before he and his mother
were sent to a hospital
once they were detained by
Customs and Border Protection.
I want to remind everybody
that CBP was touting,
for quite some time,
that no child had died
in their custody for 10 years.
And since the Trump Administration began,
six children have died in CBP custody
over that period of time.
This is just more details
about one of those cases,
specifically, and it
raises a lot of red flags
about why these children aren't
getting treatment sooner.
We now see all of these
overcrowding conditions.
All the conditions that a child like this
would have been held in.
But again, the question remains:
Why aren't they getting help sooner?
- All right.
The Daily Beast is reporting
that ICE agents told,
said "Happy Hunting" as they prepared for
a nationwide immigration
raid coming after July 4th.
Tell me about that.
- Well, I wanna be clear about
this report in particular.
"Happy hunting" referred
to immigration raids
that were supposed to happen back in 2017,
and this is not an isolated use
of this dehumanizing
phrase, happy hunting.
Adiel Kaplan, a colleague
of ours at NBC News,
has also reported that
the phrase happy hunting
was also used by Border Patrol agents
who were going to be
doing random spot checks
on Greyhound buses and other
modes of transportation
in the northeast of the United States
within what's called that 100-mile zone
that the Border Patrol
is allowed to do searches
on public transportation.
The idea that we've seen
these Facebook reports now
of dehumanizing language
towards members of Congress
and towards immigrants in the
custody of the US Government.
That ICE agents are saying "happy hunting"
when it comes to tracking
down and conducting
what are called interior
removals inside this country.
And Border Patrol agents have
said the exact same thing
about migrants that are
potentially on buses
in the northeast of the United
States, far from the border,
certainly suggest that there is a culture
of using this type of language within CBP
and we have not yet
seen a response from CBP
about this most recent report
from The Daily Beast, Ali.
- All right, Jacob, thank you
for your reporting, as always.
Jacob Soboroff for us in Los Angeles.
Coming up next, the tanks have arrived!
President Trump is being
accused of militarizing
and politicizing the national
July 4th celebration.
We'll look at his plans and
the cost for the festivities.
You're watching Velshi
& Ruhle live on MSNBC.
- In America every car is a
declaration of independence.
And to celebrate our nation's birthday,
we'll do it at Daytona.
In a 200-mile-an-hour blur
of red, white and blue.
(driving rock music)
- [Announcer] Always there in crunch time.
- [Narrator] Paul, you're
the greatest neighbor.
You help us find the best
home-improvement pros,
get quotes and research
prices for our home projects.
- That.
That's not me.
That's HomeAdvisor.
- [Narrator] You can't expect
your neighbors to do it all,
so just ask HomeAdvisor.
- [Announcer] July 4th
lands on a Thursday.
- I got it.
- [Announcer] So bookers are
booking a one, two, three,
that's a four-day weekend!
- Awesome.
- [Announcer] And with getaway
deals on accommodations
starting from 15% off,
you can be a booker at booking.com.
- [Woman] If you have
moderate to severe psoriasis,
little things can be a big deal.
That's why there's Otezla.
Otezla is not a cream.
It's a pill that treats
plaque psoriasis differently.
With Otezla, 75% clearer
skin is achievable.
Don't use if you're allergic to Otezla.
It may cause severe
diarrhea, nausea or vomiting.
Otezla is associated with an
increased risk of depression.
Tell your doctor if you have a history
of depression or suicidal thoughts,
or if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor your weight
and may stop treatment.
Upper respiratory tract infection
and headache may occur.
Tell your doctor about your medicine
and if you're pregnant or planning to be.
Ready to threat differently with a pill?
Otezla, show more of you.
- I feel like I've been
on a diet my entire life.
- I even cut out bread
and pasta for a day.
- And then I tried Noom.
- It's different.
It's more of something that
I can actually live with.
I wouldn't even call it a diet.
- I feel like anyone can use Noom.
- It was super easy.
- Super easy.
- It's an easy-to-stick-to program
that actually changed my habits.
It changed the way I look at food.
- They say it's based on a
cognitive behavioral approach.
I just say it works.
- [Woman] Visit noom.com and
lose the weight for good.
- Did you know even the
cleanest-looking cars
can smell musty.
That's because odors trapped
in your car's soft surfaces
get released and are then
circulated by your AC system.
To stop the cycle of odors,
try Febreze CAR Vent Clips.
Febreze stops the circulation of musty air
by trapping and eliminating
lingering odor molecules
for up to 30 days of fresh clean air.
Plus, they come in a range of scents,
including Extra Light.
Stop the cycle of odors in your car
with Febreze CAR Vent.
- This is a legal alert for users
of Roundup Weed Killer.
In July 2018 a judge determined
that all federal lawsuits
could move forward against Monsanto,
the maker of Roundup Weed Killer,
over concerns that those
exposed are at risk
for developing Non-Hodgkin's Lymphoma.
And in three landmark verdicts,
the most recent in May
of 2019 for $2 billion,
one in March 2019 for 80 million
and another in August
2018 for 289 million,
it was concluded that
Roundup was responsible
for the plaintiffs Non-Hodgkin's Lymphoma.
Roundup Weed Killer is
the most commonly used
weed killer in American agriculture,
with an estimated 85 to 90
million pounds used each year.
If you or someone you
love has been diagnosed
with Non-Hodgkin's Lymphoma
after being exposed
to Roundup, or a glyphosate herbicide,
you may be entitled to compensation.
How do you fight for the
compensation you deserve?
You choose the right legal team,
that has the experience and resources
to seek the most compensation
for your injuries.
Call for a free case review.
- [Announcer] Free today at homelight.com.
- Welcome back to Velshi & Ruhle.
Tomorrow we celebrate the
United States 243rd birthday
and President Trump is preparing
for his Salute to America event.
It's a very different kind of celebration
than what Washington DC is used to
as tanks and armored
personnel carriers arrived
in the Capital on flatbed
trucks over the past few days.
The president is touting the
present of M4 Sherman tanks,
which are World War II-era vehicles
he describes as brand new,
along with the more
modern M1 Abrams tanks.
APCs, represented by the
Bradley Fighting vehicle,
will also flank the ceremony.
The president's event is gonna take place
at the Lincoln Memorial,
where a source tells NBC News
he'll give remarks described
as uplifting and patriotic,
but not political.
Joining me now, NBC Pentagon
correspondent Courtney Kube.
Courtney, let's talk about the logistics
of the military display.
This isn't typical.
What's been the reaction from the Petagon?
It's been very complicated to get some
of these big tanks into DC.
- Yeah, absolutely.
Well, you have to remember,
that when you have something like
an Abrams tank that weighs tons and tons,
you can't just can't drive
it down a normal street.
It's actually not uncommon
for large military vehicles
to be moved via rail.
You know, if you go to
some of these bases,
we were down in Camp
Lejeune a couple months ago,
they have railway tracks where
they move some of their larger vehicles.
So that's what they did here.
They brought these Abrams tanks up
from Fort Stewart in Georgia, via rail,
and then they stuck on flatbeds
and drove them into the city,
because they were so
concerned about the weight,
but also the treads.
You know, these are tracked vehicles
and the treads can tear up the street.
You know, there's been a lot of question
about how is the Pentagon?
How are military leaders reacting to this?
There's been widespread
concern from military leaders
and officials who we've spoken to
over the past several months.
Since the idea of this parade even came up
and making it dedicated to the military
and having a large military involvement.
But at the end of the day,
the Pentagon lawyers reviewed
the plan and they approved it,
and they said this is an appropriate thing
for the US military to participate in
and to be apart of Ali.
- Is there any, I just
want to be clear on this,
if the military had a problem with it,
would they be compelled to send people?
- Uh, no.
I mean, if they had a problem with it
and it was considered to
be an illegal activity,
they of course would
not be involved in it.
If the attorneys found out
that there was some way
be a conflict of interest for them.
But you know as I said, it's not.
And so the military is participating.
There's also been some questions sbout
why is it that some of
the more senior members
of the Joint Chiefs aren't attending?
Like Army Chief of Staff Mark Milley.
The Commandant of the Marine
Corps, General Neller.
Well, we've been told by
numerous military officials,
of course we've been asking all week
who's gonna be attending?
And the reality is,
this came up kind of at the
last minute, this parade,
and a lot of these
people already had plans.
Some of them plan to be out of town.
Some of them plan to be on leave.
You know, Fourth of July isn't
a traditional military holiday,
in that the military
participate in a lot of events,
so a lot of these guys
planned to take time off, Ali.
- Yeah.
Courtney, thank you for
your reporting on this.
We'll keep a close eye on it.
Courtney Kube joining
us from the Pentagon.
Joining us now,
California Democratic
Congressman Gil Cisneros.
He's a member of the Armed Services
and Veterans' Affairs Committee.
He is a veteran himself.
Congressman, good to see you.
Thank you for joining us.
- Well, thank you for having me.
- We have been discussing,
as you've heard,
concern that the president's
Fourth of July celebration
is heavy on military
pageantry and could feel
more like a taxpayer-funded
campaign rally.
What's your take on this?
I mean, do you have a view about
the military participation?
There is always a parade.
This one just seems to have
a bit more of a military component,
and a bit more of a political component.
- Well, the Fourth of July should be about
celebrating our independence,
celebrating democracy.
You know, for celebrating our military,
we have Veterans' Day.
I think what he's doing
right now is turning
this event into a spectacle.
That's not that something
that we need and,
like your last guest just said,
a lot of the generals
aren't gonna be there
because they already made plans.
Unfortunately for these service members,
they're gonna have to
be there with the tanks.
They're gonna have to be there
with this aircraft for the flyovers.
The plans that they had
made had to be canceled
and now they're gonna have to
spend it here on the parade
instead of spending it with
their families and friends.
- All right, we're hearing
that the DNC didn't get
any tickets to the president's event.
We heard Kellyanne Conway
saying it's a public event.
What do you know about this?
- Well, I know I wasn't
offered any tickets,
to offer anything to my constituents.
You know, this is what
this president is doing.
He's turning it into, basically,
a campaign rally for himself.
This is not what the Fourth of
July is supposed to be about.
This is supposed to be
a non-partisan event.
It's supposed to be celebrating
the birth of our nation,
the birth of our democracy.
And, really, he's turning into an event
completely for himself.
Somewhere that he can highlight himself.
In which I'm sure he will use.
We'll see some of these highlights
in campaign footage later on.
- Let's talk about immigration.
You are in the Congressional
Hispanic Caucus.
A group that has been very, very upset
about the way things are going
in these detention centers,
and at the border generally.
What's your sense of
Congress' plan to take action?
We saw this Inspector General's report
from the Department of Homeland Security.
Which is scathing and
flies right in the face
of what DHS officials and
leaders of these very departments
and the administration has been saying
about these detention centers.
The DHS report is right in
line what our reporters,
and what you members of
Congress have been reporting
about these centers,
and in complete contrast to what
the administration is saying.
- Well, the DHS report is just confirming
what we've been hearing all along.
That the situation down there
in these facilities is atrocious.
You know, we're treating these individuals
who are coming here to this country
just trying to seek a better life
for themselves, for their families.
We're treating them worse than we treat
prisoners in our penitentiaries.
It's something that needs to change
and that why I couldn't
support the Appropriations,
the Border Appropriation Supplemental Bill
that passed through the House,
passed through the Senate last week
that the president's gonna sign.
It wasn't gonna change any
of the policies were going.
It's gonna be business as usual for CBP.
Business as usual for
Homeland Security, for ICE.
And we need real action
that's gonna really change
the conditions that's going
on in these facilities.
- But 4.3 billion dollars,
that can't be business as usual, right?
That can't possibly be.
- Well, I think a lot of it is gonna go.
We know what they were doing.
There's nothing in that bill
that's gonna change what was going on.
There's nothing that's
gonna change the standards.
gonna make it mandatory
that they see a physician.
I mean, we're hearing about these children
are dying because nobody's looked at them.
They have the flu.
They have things that
could be treated simply,
that we have the medication,
the medicine to do,
and they're not getting that treatment,
and there's nothing that was in this bill
that's gonna change that policy at all.
- Okay, I understand what you're saying.
It doesn't change policy.
But it does fund things that we understand
had problems with funding.
I guess I worry about what you think of
as a very good humanitarian bill,
that may not be achievable
and voting against one
that was achievable.
- Well, this is the thing that we need
to keep pushing for, right, in the House.
And it's something that
I'm gonna be vocal about,
is we need to kind of keep pushing for
the humanitarian treatment
of these individuals
that are in these facilities.
We need to make sure
they can see a physician.
We need to make sure that
they're gonna get hot meals.
That it's not a bologna sandwich.
And again, it's good that
they're gonna be able
to get more bologna sandwiches,
but that's not what they need.
We need something, we need policy,
we need to change a bill that's
gonna actually change policy
to make sure that these
children see a doctor.
To make sure that the families
are getting a hot meal.
That they're gonna have a toothbrush.
That they're gonna be able
to get a shower there.
- Congressman, thanks for
the time you've taken.
I appreciate it.
Congreessman Gil Cisneros is a member of
the Armed Services and
Veterans' Committee.
All right.
President Trump has long
promised to slash drug prices
and has said they're coming down.
For facts sake, thousands
of drug prices have gone up
during his administration.
We're gonna look at which common drugs
have seen the biggest spike.
You are watching Velshi
& Ruhle live on MSNBC.
♪ I'm wrapped up in a dream ♪
♪ And that dream is you ♪
- [Announcer] Are you thinking
of buying a Stairlift?
This essential, free guide
will answer all your questions.
You can find out how a
Stairlift can improve your life
in a few easy steps,
with this free guide packed
full of detailed information.
All of your questions answered!
What should I think about
when buying a Stairlift?
What type of Stairlift will suit my home?
What difference can a
Stairlift make in my life?
Answers to these, and many more,
with this free guide
to buying a Stairlift.
A Stairlift can be crucial to you
staying independent in your own home.
They were invented to
make your life easier.
And this free, practical guide,
produced with the help
of Acorn Stairlifts,
will make it easier for you to choose
the one that's right for you.
So call now, 1-800-401-5714
for your free copy
of your guide to buying a Stairlift
and have all of your Stairlift
questions answered today.
1-800-401-5714.
- At Angie's List, we
help you feel confindent
about hiring pros for home projects.
You can check their ratings,
read verified reviews,
and easily request multiple quotes.
Find all the pros you need
to know at angieslist.com.
- Hi, I'm Dana Loesch from The Dana Show.
If you could be more heart healthy
just by drinking a glass of
earthy vegetable juice daily,
would you do it?
Probably not.
But what if this
performance enhancing veggie
was transformed into a great-tasting,
circulation super-food drink?
It's called SuperBeets and I
can help you try it risk free.
See, SuperBeets helps boost
your body's nitrous oxide levels,
and that helps increase
your energy and stamina.
It supports healthy blood pressure, too.
I drink SuperBeets in
the morning for energy.
At the gym for extra-long workouts.
In the afternoon as a pick-me-up
without jittery side effects.
Get a bonus 30-day supply
free with your first order.
Plus, get the book "Beet the Odds" free
and free shipping, too.
It's guaranteed or your
gonna get your money back.
You'll love it.
- I immediately felt like
I was 10 years younger.
- Within, you know, 30
minutes of taking it
I felt a difference.
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-409-0284
or go to superbeetslove.com.
- [Woman] Constipation
can happen all around us.
You just need to know where to look.
It can happen where people drive.
It can happen where people play.
It can happen where people exercise.
Constipation can even
happen where people work.
And it happens to all of us.
Luckily, there's Colace for gentle relief
of occasional constipation.
It's the number one, doctor-recommended
stool softener brand.
Constipation happens.
(funky keyboard music)
- [Announcer] As your life
grows, so do your needs.
And with Bank of America and Merrill
the benefits you get can grow, too.
As a Preferred Rewards Member,
you can enjoy priority service
and exclusive discounts,
so your growing life can
be more rewarding, too.
What would you like the power to do?
- President Trump has
been promising to lower
prescription drug prices,
but it appears that some
are actually spiking.
For facts sake, the
government's own data shows
prices increased by 1.2% in May compared
to the same month last year.
New analysis by RX Savings Solutions,
it's a consultant for
employers and for health plans,
shows that the price of
more than 3,400 drugs
increased on an average of 17% compared
to the same time last year.
17%!
What else in your life is up 17%?
The average hike was about 10.5%,
or about five times the rate of inflation,
or about five times the rate by which
your paycheck may have gone
up over the same period.
At least 41 drugs increased
by more than 100%.
It includes one version of fluoxetine,
which is the generic
antidepressant Prozac, up 879%!
This is a generic.
Mometasone, which is a
topical steroid cream,
increased by 381%,
Promethazine/Codeine, a pain
reliever and cough medication,
went up 326%.
In fact, just this past Monday,
20 companies raised the
list prices of more than
104 prescription drugs an average of 13%.
One of them is a drug called isolyte.
It's a saline solution that's been used
to hydrate patients in
hospitals for years,
essentially salt water, it was up 100%.
With me now NBC Medical
Corespondent Dr. John Torres
to explain some of this stuff.
John, good to see you.
- Good to see you as well.
- I dwell in economics,
you dwell in medicine.
I can never figure out
how to make sense of drugs
and the costs and the increases.
- And I don't think you're alone,
and you're very well informed.
Yet, you go to the
pharmacy, you get your drug,
you try to pay for it and you find out,
the same drug you used a year ago,
all of a sudden has doubled in price,
and you don't really know why.
And I think the word
you're gonna hear a lot
coming up in the next few months
and next few years is transparency.
And I think that's the
biggest problem we have here
is those drug prices aren't transparent
and nobody really has any idea
how those prices are even set.
How the insurance companies
decide what to charge.
And then we have these things called PBMs.
They're kind of the middleman.
- Pharmacy Benefit Managers.
- Exactly.
They take their cut as well,
and so there's a lot of hands in that pie
trying to find out how to get money,
and I think that's part of the issue.
- The PBMs are negotiating
with drug makers.
They're negotiating with your health plan,
your insurance company and the pharmacies,
and that's sort of the black box.
We don't know what happens in there.
- Exactly, and it is a black box,
because magic goes on in there
and all of a sudden a drug price pops out.
And that drug price can
change from month to month
and people see that all the time.
- And different for you and me
and someone paying cash
and someone with a coupon.
- It completely depends on your insurance
or whether you have insurance or not.
What it is.
You can even have the same insurance,
but have different
contracts in that insurance
and getting charged
different amounts of money.
You just don't know.
- As a journalist in 2019,
we are able to and have to
be critical of the president
and the administration a lot.
But there have been a lot of people
who understand this world
who say that President Trump
has been trying to make progress on this.
It felt important to him to do so
and he is frustrated by his
Health and Human Services
secretary, Alex Azar,
who, by the way, is a
former drug executive,
for not getting more done.
What do we know about what's going on?
What efforts there are to
bring these prices down
when what we're seeing
is the prices go up?
- So, they're trying to
bring these prices down,
but they're trying to do it piecemeal.
So, they go into the pharmacy
companies and saying,
"Hey, can you help lower
your prices a little bit?"
They're going to the PBMs and saying,
maybe we should make some regulations
where they're not able to get that piece
of the pie that they wanna get,
and that's gonna lower prices.
They're going to pharmacies and saying,
don't distribute them
for such a big price.
They problem is, there's
so many different entities
involved with this.
Last month, I was in Germany looking
at their healthcare system
and they have a system set up
where it's all very transparent.
Everybody comes together at
the beginning to decide one,
if it's a drug worth actually
selling in the country,
using does it help anything, and two,
what's the price we're
gonna set on this drug.
Everybody there has a
co-pay of 10 euros a month,
so no matter what drug you
get it's 10 euros a month.
And it's just the way
their system is set up.
And that's only been for
the last decade or so.
It's a new system.
- Well, we need something in this country.
This is a great drug system for people
who make money off of it,
but if you actually have to pay for drugs
in this country it's very frustrating.
Wanna hear what you think.
John, thanks very much for being with us.
And please send me an e-mail or tweet me
your thoughts on what
you think can be done
about drug prices in this country.
All right, another piece of news for you.
The legendary automobile
visionary, Lee Iacoca,
passed away Tuesday at his California home
of complications with Parkinson's.
Now, many of you will
remember Lee Iacocca.
He entered the automobile industry as
an engineering trainee for Ford Motors
when he was 22-years old.
Through a series of successes,
including with the
invention of the Mustang,
Iacocca became the president
of Ford at just 46-years old.
Now because of tensions between
Iacocca and Henry Ford II,
he left for a position with
Chrysler just eight years later
and that is a move that saved the company.
Chrysler was debt-ridden and
losing millions of dollars.
Iacocca saved the company from bankruptcy
by introducing the
fuel-efficient K-car line,
allowing the company to
make several different
models of cars on one chassis at a time.
He introduced the Chrysler Minivan,
which led the auto industry for years.
Bringing Chrysler back into competition.
Safe to say, Lee Iacocca
remade the automobile industry
before retiring in 1992.
He made his name known by
appearing in commercials.
He was listed as one of the
world's most respected men
in a mid-1980s Gallup poll,
only behind President Ronald
Reagan and Pope John Paul II.
His name even came up as a potential
presidential contender in 1988.
Lee Iacocca was 94-year old.
We'll be right back.
- [Woman on Phone] Discover.
- Hi.
Do you have a travel card?
- Yep, our Miles Card.
Earn unlimited 1.5
miles and we'll match it
at the end of your first year.
- Nice.
I'm thinking about a scuba diving trip.
- [Woman on Phone] Ooo.
- (gasps) Or not!
- You okay?
- Yeah no, I'm good.
- [Announcer] Earn miles.
We'll match 'em at the
end of your first year.
- Most homeowners draw a black when asked
what their home projects should cost.
That's why at HomeAdvisor,
you can see what others paid
for similar jobs in your area.
Start your next home project
knowing what you should pay.
Go to homeadvisor.com or
download the free app.
- [Announcer] It's only a matter of time
until your check engine light comes on
or worse yet, your car needs repair.
That could mean a big
surprise auto repair bill.
Those repairs are more
expensive than ever.
A new engine can be over $5,000.
A new transmission over $4,000.
That's why it's so important
you call CarShield today.
CarShield is the number
one auto protection company
in the country.
- I like CarShield because
they were reliable,
they were affordable and
they were trustworthy.
- Well, I think everybody
should have CarShield.
Once your manufacturer's
warranty is expired,
there's just no big bills.
We needed repairs,
CarShield was there for us.
- [Announcer] Now it's your
turn to get the peace of mind
that comes with having CarShield,
so you can worry less about auto repairs.
Call or go online right now
to get CarShield for yourself.
Friendly, knowledgeable,
money-saving representatives
are available 24-hours-a-day,
So if your car is 20-years old or newer,
just tell us the make and
model of your car or truck
to get an instant plan quote.
In a matter of minutes,
you can be covered.
- I was elated that I had CarShield.
I was more than happy.
- It's no fun when you
have a car and it's broken
and you can't pay for it to get it fixed.
- [Announcer] Here's how CarShield works.
When your car needs repair,
you take it to your favorite
mechanic or even your dealer
and CarShield gets them paid directly.
That's why CarShield
is America's number one
auto protection provider.
- CarShield is just the best
thing to take away the fear
that when something is gonna
go wrong with your car,
because it will,
and CarShield is gonna
be there to back you up.
- My experience with CarShield is that
they absolutely come through
every time I need them.
- If my car breaks down,
I can count on CarShield
to cover it for me.
CarShield definitely has my back.
- [Announcer] Now it's the
time to make the smart choice
and protect yourself from
sky high auto repair bills.
Call now for a free and
instant protection plan quote.
It's only a matter of time
until repairs are needed
and once your car breaks
down, it's too late.
Call 1-800-471-5552.
That's 1-800-471-5552.
- If something happened to
you, what would happen to them?
Their home, their education, their future.
You need life insurance
and chances are SelectQuote
can help you get it
for less than a dollar a day.
- [Announcer] SelectQuote found Jacob, 40,
a $500,000 policy for only $19 a month,
and SelectQuote found his wife Wendy
a $500,000 policy for only $17 a month.
- Our secret?
At SelectQuote, we
aggressively comparison shop
up to 10 highly-rated
companies to find you
the company with the best rates.
- [Announcer] We found Gary, 35,
a $1,000,000 policy for only $22 a month.
- Why pay more?
Give your family the security they need
at a price you can afford.
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-677-2970
or go to selectquote.com now
and get the insurance your family needs.
- [Male Voice] At a price you can afford.
SelectQuote: We shop, you save.
- [Chuck] Washington feels
more chaotic than ever.
It's my job to ask the tough
questions, left and right,
and help you make sense of it all.
- [Announcer] More
Americans watch NBC News
than any other news
organization in the world.
- Welcome back to Velshi & Ruhle.
A new NBC exclusive report suggests
the tension between Silicon Valley
and Capital Hill is intensifying.
The report details how
tech advocacy groups
are now pushing back on legislation
aimed at regulating major tech giants,
which was introduced by
a Republican senator,
Josh Hawley, last month.
AdNow, tech-focused
non-profits in DC are fearing
a quote partisan blood match between
big companies and top regulators.
Joining me now, NBC political reporter,
the one who wrote the story, Allan Smith.
Allan, what's this about?
Why is Hawley, a conservative,
the guy putting forward legislation
to regulate tech companies
and what's the larger concern?
- So first off, Senator Hawley,
a first-term senator from Missouri.
He's come in and he's
wanting to be the Republican
who's really at the forefront
of some of these tech
regulations battles, right?
He's splitting with Republican orthodoxy
and he wants to have a much more
activist government in this regard.
Now this bill that he's
proposed is super controversial,
and there's a lot of pushback from groups
that aren't directly aligned
with Google and Facebook.
What the bill would do simply is remove
some of the protections that
major tech companies enjoy
under what's known as Section 230 of
the Communications Decency Act.
- [Ali] Which was written in the 90s.
- Yes.
- And a lot of people feel that it's
a little antiquated, a little out of date.
- A little bit.
So, this law provides
freedom from liability
for these tech companies for stuff
that third-party users
post on their platform.
- [Ali] Backpage would be
the best example, right?
- Yes.
- Backpage made the argument that we're
just a site that people put stuff on.
You can't hold us liable for the content.
- Absolutely.
So, what Hawley's bill does
is it changes that immunity,
so that these companies
would have to apply for it
every two years from the
FTC, and the FTC would vote.
You would need a super majority,
four out of five commissioners would vote
if the company's practices
are quote politically neutral.
So Hawley's side says,
look with a super majority
of the FTC commissioners
having to get on board,
you would have a bi-partisan response.
But we both know, very well,
that Republicans and
Democrats don't really agree
on a definition of
politically neutral right now.
And some of these companies
could just get stuck
in this purgatory where
they're not receiving immunity,
and then you could have a
situation where, you know,
if every single piece of content
these companies could be liable for,
they'll end up with much
wider-spread censorship.
They're gonna have to review
every piece of content
that goes up on their website.
- All right.
This is definitely one
that we are going to
continue to follow with you.
Thank you Allan Smith, NBC News reporter.
We are seeing record closings on
all three major indices right now.
Might be a little early for
us to tell you about this,
but, in fact, markets closed early today
because tomorrow is the July 4th holiday.
You are looking at three new records.
The Dow is at 29,966.
Standard and Poor's just
half-a-point shy of 3,000 points
and the NASDAQ closing at
yet at yet another record,
8,170 points.
I want to talk about
Nike's latest controversy.
It's all about an historical
flag put on a shoe.
To some that flag's a symbol of hate,
to others America's revolution.
We're gonna look at
all sides of the debate
and how Nike handled the situation.
You're watching Velshi
& Ruhle live on MSNBC.
(soothing piano music)
- [Announcer] Corey is living
with metastatic breast cancer.
Which is breast cancer that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking Ibrance
with an aromatase inhibitor,
which is for post-menopausal
women or for men
with HR-positive HER2-negative
metastatic breast cancer
as the first hormonal-based therapy.
Ibrance plus letrozole was significantly
more effective at delaying
disease progression
versus letrozole.
Patients taking Ibrance can develop
low white blood cell counts,
which may cause serious
infections that can lead to death.
Before taking Ibrance, tell
your doctor if you have
fever, chills, or other
signs of infections,
liver or kidney problems,
or pregnant, breast-feeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side-effects
include low red blood cell
and low platelet counts,
infections, tireness, nausea, sore mouth,
abnormalities in
liver-blood tests, diarrhea,
hair thinning or loss, vomiting,
rash, and loss of appetite.
Corey calls it her new normal,
because a lot has changed.
But a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about Ibrance,
the number one prescribed, FDA-approved
oral combination treatment for
HR-positive/HER2-negative NBC.
(mellow piano music)
- [Announcer] It's funny what happens
when people get together.
Holiday Inn, Holiday Inn Express.
We're there, so you can be too.
- [Male Voice] Paul, you're
the greatest neighbor.
You help us find the best
home-improvement pros,
get quotes and research
prices for our home projects.
- That.
That's not me, that's HomeAdvisor.
- [Male Voice] You can't expect
your neighbors to do it all.
So just ask HomeAdvisor.
- I found a way to relieve my constipation
that's both gentle and fast.
New Dulcolax Liquid works naturally
with the water in my body
to provide gentle relief
in as little as 30 minutes.
New, stimulant-free Dulcolax Liquid.
Puts you comfortably in control.
- Going to the Shawn
Mendes Verizon Up concert
was like an out-of-body experience.
- [Announcer] Why the Yousafzai
sisters chose Verizon.
- We were right in front of him.
- Dead center, front row.
Actually Zermina, you
touched Shawn Mendes.
You touched Shawn Mendes.
- Yeah, I touched him.
He, like, held my hand for a while.
Then we got to meet him after,
which was like--
- Another surprise.
- Yeah, we love Verizon even more now.
I'll never forget that day, ever.
- [Announcer] The network
more people rely on
gives you more.
Like thousands of tickets to concerts,
festivals and private shows.
And big savings on our best phones when--
(doorbell rings)
- Oh!
Me, it can't be!
I'm not ready!
I do spin class!
What?
The refrigerator, oh come on!
Do you know how much this cost me?
You're killing me!
(suspenseful orchestral chord)
Let me rephrase that.
- [Announcer] Your
refrigerator, air conditioner,
water heater will all die sometime.
When they do, your homeowner's
insurance won't cover them.
Be sure your budget's protected with
an American Home Shield home warranty.
We help cover the cost of repair
or replace components of
your systems and appliances.
No matter their age.
Limitations and exclusions apply.
Home systems and appliances
will eventually die.
Count on American Home Shield to get you
back up and running.
- [Woman] Oh, the air conditioner, too?
- [Announcer] Be sure
your budget's protected.
For free information call 1-800-798-9543.
That's 1-800-798-9543.
Be sure with the shield.
American Home Shield.
- [Woman] At homelight.com.
- Today Nike and Colin Kaepernick are back
in the center of controversy
and this time it's over sneakers.
Nike is pulling these
shoes from its inventory,
which feature the so-called
Betsy Ross-version
of the American flag.
Now to some people, that
is a flag representing hate
and slavery because it was in place
at a time when slavery was
enshrined in the United States.
To others, it's a patriotic
symbol of the Revolutionary War.
NBC's Stephanie Gosk has more.
- [Stephanie] Nike's decision to pull
these red, white and blue shoes
emblazoned with a colonial-era flag
is whipping even more controversy.
The Governor of Arizona
threatening to pull incentives
for a Nike manufacturing
plant in his state,
calling Nike's recall
a "shameful retreat."
Adding, "words cannot
express my disappointment
"at this terrible decision."
The future of the facility,
which would employ about
500 people, is unclear.
According to The Wall Street Journal,
former NFL quarterback Colin Kaepernick
spearheaded the call to
get Nike to pull the shoe.
Citing people familiar with the matter,
the report says he was offended
by the use of the flag,
as were others.
In a statement Nike says its decision
to recall the design was
"based on concerns that
it could unitentionally
"offend and detract from the
nation's patriotic holiday."
When the iconic brand revealed
the shoe late last month,
critics spoke out, one writing,
"Nike you should be ashamed of this shoe."
Another wrote, "Can't wait for
the Confederate Air Max 90s."
The so-called Betsy Ross flag,
named after the 18th-century woman
mythologized for designing it,
has been flown at some nationalist
and American Nazi rallies.
Some say it celebrates
the time of slavery.
While others, including
Texas senator, Ted Cruz,
are renewing calls for a Nike boycott.
Cruz tweeting in part,
"Their shoes represent snide
disdain for the American flag."
Similar calls were made
when Nike partnered
with Caepernick last
year in an ad campaign.
- [Colin] Believe in something.
Even if it means sacrificing everything.
The former quarterback
was the first in the NFL
to kneel during the national anthem,
protesting police brutality
and racial injustice.
Some burned their shoes
and boycotted Nike.
While the company saw its sales rise
and it's stock price surge.
- Joining me now is NBC's Stephanie Gosk.
Stephanie, I was just saying to you,
I think that in 25 years,
when we study the
culture wars of this era,
this will be a case study.
- That's right.
The moment a sneaker is at the
center of the culture wars.
- And everybody's very dug in
on their position on this one.
- Yeah, they certainly are.
You know, you could make the argument
there's a conversation we need to have.
There are clearly people who
are on both sides of this
who are very agitated and upset for,
quite honestly, understandable reasons.
Where do we come together to talk about it
is really the crucial question.
- I was surprised in your piece,
and when I looked at the story,
to find that people associate
this so-called Betsy Ross flag.
It's not clear Betsy Ross designed it,
she may have just changed the star design,
with the same feelings that people have
for the Confederate flag.
- Right.
It's certainly not an overwhelming feeling
and something that's been in the public.
But there have been
these limited examples.
For instance, there was a
chapter of the Ku Klux Klan
that had some flyers in upstate New York
that used the flag to
try to recruit people.
- [Ali] Right.
- To their chapter.
That's obviously pretty limited.
There were a couple of
high school students
at a high school football
game a couple of years ago
that were waving the flag and then later
the superintendent came
out and apologized for that
saying that this flag had
become what he called,
"a symbol of hate."
But those were limited
examples and this controversy,
clearly the most
widespread that we've seen
when it comes to this flag.
- This hasn't really
hurt Nike stock price,
and Nike has been through controversies.
But Nike understands branding,
possibly more than most
other companies in the world.
Is it interesting that
it got to this point
without Nike having figured out that
there might be some
controversy around this.
- It is, and I also think it's a statement
on just how controversial
this flag really is.
Because like you say, branding, for Nike,
is second nature.
They have almost defined branding for us
in the modern world.
- None of us knew what that swoosh was
until they invented it.
- Of marketing, yeah.
And signing Kaepernick,
you know, in those moments
when there was a lot of criticism,
which they knew they were going to get.
The burning of the shoes
and the rest of it.
In those immediate moments after that,
they did actually see
their stock price go up and their shoe--