♪ Liberty ♪
- [Announcer] What is love?
Two hearts, one soul?
A kiss?
A hug?
A laugh?
It's passion.
It's freedom.
It's mystery.
It's the journey and the destination.
It's vows made and promises kept.
It's a feeling, a need, no rules.
All included, all unlimited.
Feed your hunger.
Quench your thirst.
Live your dreams.
Fulfilled, indulged, reborn.
What is love?
Love is all you need.
Call 1-800-Sandals.
- [Announcer] Calm today.
- All right, that wraps us
this hour of MSNBC Live.
My friend Ali Velshi is here
to pick up our coverage.
- Nice to see you again 24 hours later.
It was fun working with you yesterday
when we were covering a difficult story.
But thank you for you
coverage this afternoon.
Are you done?
- Happy to be here.
I am done.
- [Ali] All right, have yourself
a great rest of the day.
- You too.
- See you.
All right, good afternoon.
I'm Ali Velshi.
It's Friday, July 5th,
two o'clock in the East
where a deadline has just
passed for the White House
to announce whether it will keep fighting
to add a citizenship
question to the 2020 census.
A federal judge in overseeing
one of three separate lawsuits
over the question ruled that
the Trump administration
must explain how it's going
to proceed by two p.m. today.
President Trump addressed the controversy
with reporters earlier.
- [Reporter] Are you going to issue
an executive order on the census?
- We're thinking about doing that.
It's one of the ways.
We have four or five ways we can do it.
It's one of the ways
that we're thinking about
doing it very seriously.
We're doing well on the census.
(reporter mumbles)
No, he made a statement.
He wrote something up.
The judge didn't like it.
I have a lot of respect
for Justice Roberts,
but he didn't like it.
But he did say come back.
Essentially, he said come back.
That's what he was saying.
So we'll see what happens.
- [Ali] The case seemed all but
settled just a few days ago.
The Supreme Court ruled last week
that the Commerce Department's
current justification
for putting the question on the census
was not legally sound,
calling it contrived
and the government has
even begun printing copies
of the census without
the question included.
But earlier this week, the President,
reportedly spurred on
by Conservative allies,
announced on Twitter that his
administration will once again
take up the fight, sending
White House lawyers scrambling
over the holiday to come
up with a new argument.
Joining me now,
NBC News justice
correspondent Pete Williams.
Pete you had a lot of specific guidance
that you've been giving
us through the day about--
- Pardon me for,
I'm just gonna look away.
This is going to panic everyone
that's speaking to me in my ear.
I'm listening, but I'm
looking at something
that's just been filed, so go ahead.
- That's what we were waiting for.
There was a two p.m. deadline for a filing
in which the government either had to say,
"We're gonna continue on with this fight,"
or it could say, "We're not continuing."
The two p.m. deadline,
the most important thing
that would happen is if we
heard the government say
we're giving it up.
- Can you bring that to me?
- So that's essentially
what we're waiting for.
If the government doesn't
choose to withdraw
its fight to add a citizenship question,
then things continue as they are.
The census will be printed.
The government will have
to figure out a new way
to get it on there, and
that may not happen.
- So this is what's, just a second ago,
been filed by the government.
And no surprise here, they say,
"We're gonna keep fighting."
They filed what they call
their proposed discovery plan
and what they say is they
lay out a schedule for
how to continue in this Maryland lawsuit,
the separate lawsuit from
the Supreme Court case
on the census form.
So no surprise here,
the government says it
wants to continue fighting.
- So while you read that,
here's what I wanna lay out.
The government says it's
gonna continue fighting.
For the moment, the
government continues to print
the census forms, because that
was the argument they used,
that they needed a judgment or at least
some kind of guidance
from the Supreme Court
before June 30th in order
to print these forms.
So those forms continue to be printed.
The government's not giving up its fight.
Logistically, Pete,
(Pete chuckles)
what happens next?
- Okay.
- What can happen?
- All right, so here are the options
based on what I've just been able to read
from what the government has filed
and what the other side
in this case has filed.
So first, we have the Supreme Court case.
That was started from a
lawsuit filed by 18 states,
led by New York, went
to the US Supreme Court.
Last week, the Supreme
Court said this explanation
that Commerce Secretary Wilbur Ross gave
for why he wanted the
question in the form,
clearly, it doesn't wash.
It's a pretext.
You can't print the
census if that's the basis
for wanting it on the form.
So the Supreme Court has
ordered the government
not to print the census
with that question on it.
And in fact, it's now printing
it without that question.
So what are the alternatives?
One is Wilbur Ross could come up
with a new justification for it
that would start a whole
new round of litigation.
The government clearly thinks
that's not a very productive way
because they thought earlier
this week, it was all over,
and then the President said,
"You gotta keep trying."
Another possibility that the
President himself raised today
is the President simply
signs an executive order
directing the Commerce Department
to tell the Census Bureau
to put this question on the form.
That, again, would start a
whole new round of litigation.
Anything the government does
from hereon is--
- Let's just stop
at that one for a second,
an executive order.
The President, this president
certainly believes it,
and by the way, he's not the
first president to think so,
that certain things can be
done by executive order.
But is the President clear
that an executive order
to put the question on
the census doesn't mean
that the census gets printed
with the citizenship question on it?
- Correct.
It's not gonna do it by
itself because that will
immediately produce
another court challenge.
Anything the government does from hereon
is gonna produce a court challenge.
That's a certainty.
So back to your question,
using the word logistics,
how long would that take?
How long does the government
have before it really can't?
It has to just keep printing
the forms without the question.
I don't think anybody
has a good clear answer
to when the final drop dead date is
for not tinkering around
with this thing any further.
It's gonna cost a lot of
money if they throw away
all the forms they've already
printed and start over again.
Another option though would be
to either include this
citizenship question
on the longer form, the
household survey that goes
to just a small percentage
of US households,
or an additional form,
an additional question
that goes with the short form
that goes to all households,
just a simple piece of paper that says,
"Are you a US citizen, yes or no,"
what they wanted to put on
the form in the first place.
Now that too, I think,
will lead to litigation
because the groups opposed to this say
it would have the same
kind of chilling effect.
But, you know, as we think
through all this, remember,
no matter what you may think
of this as a policy matter,
whether it's a wise thing
to put this on the form,
whether it will lead to an under count,
or whether it will give
us more information,
that's a balancing test,
just recall that throughout
most censuses in American history,
there has been a citizenship question.
So the government has
some weight on its side
if it can come up with a rationale
that satisfies these challenges.
Now one other point.
The President said
today, when he was asked,
"Why do you want this
question on the form,"
said, "Well, you need it to figure out
"how many seats a state
gets in the House."
That is demonstrably not true.
No apportionment throughout our history,
and we've just celebrated
another birthday,
has ever been based on
just counting citizens.
It's always been total inhabitants.
And that was clear from the
constitutional convention
and clear from when Congress
enacted the 14th Amendment
which gave further guidance
on how to conduce a census.
So in that sense, you
don't need citizenship data
to apportion a membership in the house.
- Pete, I'm gonna give you the option.
You can hang out with me while
I bring Barbara McQuade in.
I do know that you have
some reading to do.
So you're welcome to sit
in front of that camera
and do the reading.
And if you hear something
you want, chime in.
- Okay.
- Let's bring
former US Attorney from the
Eastern District of Michigan,
Barbara McQuade in.
Barbara, there's a lot
to get through here.
This seemed like a simple
question at one time.
Can you put the citizenship
question on the census or not?
Now it's gotten complicated
because the Supreme Court said
that the Commerce Department's reasoning
was not appropriate for doing so.
But they didn't say that
means, to Pete's earlier point,
that a citizenship question
can't be on the census.
Basically, the Supreme Court
said to the government,
"You can come back with a
better reason and try again."
- Well, they can, but it
has to be a genuine reason.
And what the court found was
that the reason that they gave,
that the purpose was so that
they could better comply
with the Voting Rights Act,
was a lie, was a pretext.
The word they used was contrivance.
And they said, "If you wanna try again
"and tell us the real
reason, we'll consider that."
But it's hard to imagine
that they could come back
and say, "Oh, when we told you
"it was about the Voting Rights
Act, we just made a mistake.
"The real reason was the following."
It's hard to imagine that any
new reason they came up with,
you know, my dog ate it,
is something that could be believed.
And so it's hard to
imagine, going forward,
that there's going to be
a path to victory here
for President Trump.
- Now, there's another issue,
and that is that the government's lawyers
went to the Supreme Court and
said, "We kinda need this done
"in a hurry because we gotta
print these forms by June 30th
"in order to get them printed
and distributed on time."
Now, when you go back to the
Supreme Court and you say,
"Yeah, you know that deadline
"we told you we really needed it done by.
"Because we have different reasons,
"we can push that deadline."
Does that affect the credibility
of the government's lawyers
in front of the Supreme Court?
Or is that not important?
- No, it absolutely does.
And every lawyer who works
for the Department of Justice
knows that not only like
every lawyer do they have
a duty of candor to the tribunal,
but the Justice Department
has an even higher duty,
as lawyers on behalf of the United States,
to tell the truth.
And in fact, here, it wasn't
just a passing statement
that they made that could be characterized
as a slip of the tongue.
They actually affirmatively
said, "We don't have time
"to go through the normal
route of the Second Circuit
"Court of Appeals because
time is of the essence
"and this is of such public
importance that we need to skip
"that ordinary step and go
directly to the Supreme Court
"because June 30th is
our absolute deadline
"for getting these things printed."
To now go back and say, "We made that up,"
I think would harm the Justice Department
not only in this case,
but the Justice Department
every other case it litigates
everyday around the country.
- [Ali] Pete?
- Well, just this is a very short thing
that the government filed here,
and I don't think it really changes
a lot of what we've said, but
just to amplify one thing.
They say, "Right, Judge.
"We're currently enjoined in
printing a census questionnaire
"that includes the citizenship question.
"We're not doing it.
"But any new decision by
the Commerce Department
"on providing another rationale
for why it wants to do this
"would constitute a new
final agency action,
"and plaintiffs will be fully entitled
"to challenge the decision at that time."
So that goes back to what
we were saying earlier, Ali,
that if the Commerce Secretary says,
"Oh, now, here's why I wanna do it,"
that will lead to another
round of litigation.
So all they say is in the event
the Commerce Department
adopts a new rationale,
the government will
immediately notify this court,
that's the judge in
Maryland, so it can determine
whether there's any need for
further proceedings or relief.
So that's the separate
Maryland case that did not go
to the Supreme Court
that's still simmering.
- All right.
Thank you for your
great reporting on this,
Pete Williams and Barbara McQuade.
Thank you for your excellent
analysis, as always.
Barbara McQuade is a former US Attorney
for the Eastern District of Michigan.
Pete Williams, our justice
reporter who'll continue
to report on this as he
gets through the documents.
All right, if it's the
first Friday of the month,
it must be jobs day,
and June's job numbers
appear to be a correction
from May's dismal showing.
224,000 net new jobs
were added last month.
That's a good number.
Don't let anybody tell you otherwise.
Unemployment ticked up
slightly from 3.6 to 3.7%.
Hourly earnings are up
3.1%, year over year.
Now, that looks pretty good.
Remember that you always
have to subtract inflation from that.
All eyes are now on the Federal Reserve
where Chairman Jerome Powell
is going to have to decide
whether or not these numbers
warrant slashing interest rates.
Joining me now, CNBC's John Harwood.
I mean, this is a tough one
for the President to spin
because on one hand, he really,
he likes the job numbers
almost as much as he likes
the stock market numbers.
But touting strong job
numbers means that the Fed
now has to reconsider whether
or not to cut interest rates,
which the President really
wants the Fed to do.
- That's right, Ali.
It won't constraint the President.
He's gonna continue to
want that interest rate cut
because growth in the
economy is slowing from 2018,
and he wants it to rev up again
going into the 2020 election year.
But the Fed, which weighs
data, has got to figure out
whether or not this indicates
that it would be too early
to make a rate cut in light
of these jobs numbers.
We did have a downward
revision on April and June,
or excuse me, April and May,
so that is a negative in that picture.
But nevertheless, these are good numbers.
And Jay Powell, in his
last press conference,
said that they removed the word
patience from their guidance
and they indicated that they
were going to be inclined,
if the data suggested, to
cut rates one or more times
in the rest of the year,
but this makes that
decision more difficult.
- You know, the one thing
that the President wants
is he wants to goose those growth numbers.
They are a little slower.
We do not appear to be
in recession territory
or even close to it at this point,
but they're smaller than they were,
and they're smaller than
the President had promised
when he ran in his election.
If you recall, he said, "My
economists think it will be 3%.
"I think it could be 4, 5 and 6%."
That is the one lever that
the government has, in theory.
If you lower interest rates,
it's like hitting the gas
pedal on the economy, right?
That's the thing that can
cause growth to increase,
because it becomes
cheaper to borrow money.
Money is more available.
People invest.
They build plants.
They buy houses, things like that.
That's right.
And it's all the more important
for him to hit the gas pedal
since his other foot's hitting
the brake with the trade war.
The uncertainty and the
friction with China,
the disruption of supply chains,
the higher consumer prices
as a result pose some risk to the economy.
It's not clear whether
or not if you cut rates,
that that would work on the same timeframe
that the trade war is
doing to the economy,
but the fact that he's
pulled back a little bit
in recent days from conflict with China,
that in itself is good
news for the economy.
And this is one way he
can make it go faster
if Jay Powell decides to go along.
But of course, Jay Powell is independent,
and I think he values his
reputation for independence,
so he'll make his own decision.
- John, you had a chance to
sit down with Beto O'Rourke
and talk about some of
his economic policies.
- Let me ask you about your experience
as a small businessman,
both the web services
company, the alt weekly.
Do you look upon that as a success?
And what do you take from
it as you think about
the economic challenges of the country?
- Yeah.
So I do look at it as
a success, to be able,
with good friends, far more
talented, smarter than I was,
to come together and
create opportunity and jobs
in the third poorest urban
county in the United States,
high-value, high-skill,
high-tech jobs in El Paso, Texas.
That felt really good.
It was really hard to
do, but I'll tell you,
I had some advantages that
other Americans don't.
And I'll give you an example.
I could not get a loan in 1998
to start a technology company in El Paso.
I just didn't have the assets
that the bank would lend against.
But my dad, who had a home
that was fully paid for,
could take out a loan on his home
and then lend that money
back to me, 20,000 bucks.
That was the seed capital
that allowed us to start
a business, that ultimately
hired dozens of our fellow
El Pasoans and served clients
all over this country.
- You know, John, I often think
that people who have
small business experience
could be very useful to our country.
You don't have to have
macroeconomic experience.
What was your takeaway?
Because you talk to people
about business and economics
and their understanding
of it all the time.
- Well, that's a selling point
for Beto O'Rourke in this race.
He started a business.
It's still going 20 years later.
It was a profitable business.
The publishing, the alt
weekly that he founded
went out of business, but
the tech services company
that he's no longer an owner of it
is continuing to operate.
The point he went on to
make in that discussion
was that he is mindful
that very few Americans
have families that can
stake them to $20,000
to start a small business.
A lot of his small business proposals
are designed to extend more
credit, more tax incentives
to communities of color
where wealth inequality
has suppressed the
formation of small business,
and that's a big talking
point for him in the race.
- I skipped lunch, which is a bad idea,
and I kept watching you
while you were eating
and trying to figure out what you ate.
What were you eating?
- I was eating the enchilada platter,
half red sauce, half green sauce.
It was delicious.
He had tacos, though as
you can see, he was talking
most of the time and not
inclined to pick 'em up.
- [Ali] I enjoy interview like that,
where someone else is
talking and I'm eating.
- [John] Right. (chuckles)
- And good to see you, my friend.
Thank you, John Harwood--
- You bet, thank you.
- Editor-at-large at CNBC.
All right, still to come,
the President once again
blames the border crisis on Democrats,
saying they're treating
border agents unfairly.
He even accused some lawmakers of lying.
I'll get the reaction
from Texas Democrat
Congressman Marc Veasey
who toured border facilities this week.
But first, Joe Biden
admits he was blindsided
by Kamala Harris's confrontation
at the first debate,
and why Biden says despite sliding polls,
he's still the best pick
to take on Donald Trump.
- Hi.
- [Woman] Look at how great you look.
- Thank you. (chuckles)
- I feel like I've been
on a diet my entire life.
- I even cut out bread and pasta
for a day.
- And then I tried Noom.
- I feel like anyone could use Noom.
- It's an easy to stick to program
that actually changed by habits.
It changed the way I looked at food.
- They say it's based on a
cognitive behavioral approach.
I just say it works.
- It just clicked.
It worked.
It worked with Noom.
- [Announcer] Visit noom.com
and lose the weight for good.
- [Announcer] This is not just any cruise.
This MSC Cruises, one of
the largest cruise lines
in the world, where every
detail is beyond just ordinary.
You won't walk on just any stairs.
These steps are covered
in Swarovski crystals.
There's not just one performance to see.
There's a different show every night.
On an MSC Cruise, you won't
be served just any meal.
You'll enjoy freshly prepared
international cuisine.
And you won't explore just any destination
or experience just any ship.
You'll cruise the Caribbean
on the best new cruise ship,
the revolutionary MSC Seaside.
Book a seven-night Caribbean cruise
and get unlimited drinks and
Wi-Fi from only 549 per person.
That's right.
Get unlimited drinks,
including wine, beer,
missed drinks and more.
Call MSC Cruises at 800-615-0726.
Visit msccruises.com or
your travel agent today.
- Going to the Shawn
Mendes Verizon Up concert
was like an out-of-body experience.
- [Announcer] Why the Yousafzai
sisters chose Verizon.
- We were right in front of him.
- Dead center, front row.
Actually, Zamila, you
touched Shawn Mendes.
- She touched Shawn Mendes.
- Yeah, I touched him.
He like held my hand for a while,
and then we got to meet
him after, which was like--
- Another surprise.
- Yeah.
We love Verizon even more now.
I'll never forget that day ever.
- [Announcer] The network
more people rely on
gives you more, like thousands of tickets
to concerts, festivals and private shows,
and big savings on our best phones when--
(upbeat music)
- So what?
So let's dance!
(upbeat music)
♪ Limu emu ♪
- [Announcer] And Doug.
- What do all these people
have in common Limu.
Exactly.
Nothing.
They're completely different people.
That's why they need
customized car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay for what they need.
Yes, and they could save a ton.
You've done it again, Limu.
- [Announcer] Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty, Liberty ♪
♪ Liberty ♪
- [Announcer] To the fullest.
- Isn't this a situation of
hate the game, not the player?
- This is a power play.
This is a strategic move from her, right?
- Why is this potentially such a big deal?
- We have more breaking news.
Why wouldn't we?
It's Tuesday in Washington.
- The wall is the sticking
point, not border security.
- Although the promise was
a wall paid for by Mexico.
- I cannot wait to keep
talking about 2020.
I gotta tell you, I
think it's fascinating.
- Your entire business is profiting
off of other people's information,
then your job is to keep
that information safe.
All right, as the Democratic
presidential candidates
race to qualify for the next debate,
we've got new fundraising
numbers to report.
Moments ago, Senator
Kamala Harris's campaign
announced it raised nearly $12 million
in the second quarter.
Still in the lend, South
Bend, Indiana mayor,
Pete Buttigieg's campaign announced Monday
it raised $24.8 million.
Front runner Biden trails him
with $21.5 million in the quarter.
Montana governor Steve Bullock,
only entered the race in
mid-May and mid-quarter,
has raised a surprising $2 million.
Former Vice President
Joe Biden is addressing
those fiery debate
comments from 2020 opponent
Senator Kamala Harris
criticizing his decades-old
senate fight against
desegregation of busing
and his comments on working
with segregationist senators.
In a new CNN interview,
Biden said Harris's
comments were unexpected.
- I mean, it's so easy to go back
and go back 30, 40, 50
years and take a context
and take it completely out of context.
And I mean, you know, I
get all this information
about other people's past and
what they've done and not done
and you know, I'm just not gonna go there.
- Biden also expresses confidence
in defeating President Trump.
A new Quinnipiac University national poll
shows his 42% lead in that category.
- The idea that I'd be
intimidated by Donald Trump,
he's the bully that I knew my whole life.
He's the bully that
I've always stood up to.
He's the bully who used to
make fun when I was a kid
and stuttered and I'd
smack them in the mouth.
- All right, joining me now
is NBC political reporter, Ali Velshi,
just in time for this afternoon's
Ali V segment, Ali Vitali.
I guess that would be your name.
I'd be Ali Velshi.
It gets confusing.
- It's okay.
- Ali V,
talk to me about Harris's
campaign talking about
what Joe Biden said, saying
this wasn't an attack.
- Well, it clearly was an attack.
And I think that they were
definitely prepared for it.
You and I have talked about this before.
And Lily Adams was on CNN
today basically saying
the fact that he wasn't prepared for it,
she's not quite sure why that happened,
but the Kamala Harris campaign came in,
and this is what debates are,
to kind of separate the field
and show the differences.
I do think that there's a
reticence on Joe Biden's part
to be apologetic for his past record.
And it's difficult to run on
this argument of electability
and experience when you're
not really ready to defend
the experience portion of it,
specifically when you look
at 30 years of policymaking decisions.
Things look different
over the course of time.
And I covered a candidate
who was reticent to apologize in the past.
Joe Biden is not Donald Trump.
And so I think that this is
a strategy that I'm not sure
how effective it's going
to be going down the line
in this campaign as there are
gonna be a lot more policies
that come up about Joe Biden's past
that the other candidates
are gonna want to litigate.
- Harris, the polling
that we were showing,
seems to be closing the gap.
That new Quinnipiac University poll
shows her numbers have surged 13 points.
Joe Biden's have surged eight points.
But in a different question,
when people are asked
who can beat Donald Trump,
Joe Biden's still way ahead.
I guess to some degree, Kamala
Harris taking on Joe Biden
in that debate was about showing
I can beat a front runner.
- Maybe.
I think that for a lot of the candidates
on that stage with Joe
Biden, the reason why
the conventional thinking
was that it's a good thing
to share the debate stage
with him is because obviously,
a lot of eyes are looking at him.
When you're coming into
this race as Joe Biden
or Bernie Sanders, you have
a high name recognition.
So that's why I think in a
lot of these early polls,
you're seeing them so far out ahead.
They have leads now to defend.
For the other candidates,
it's a matter of introducing themselves
to an electorate that may not be aware
of all these other candidates
that are in the race now.
And so when you see
these polls tightening,
I actually don't know
that it's rising levels of
support and not support.
I actually think it's just
the electorate tuning in
and showing that they're becoming
aware of different people.
I think that as we get
further down the line,
we're gonna see a debate in
July, a debate in September,
that's when we're gonna start to see
a lot more of the awareness
coming into the polls.
After that, I'd feel comfortable
looking at polls and saying,
all right, these are
trends that are sticking.
- Yeah, this is for us right now,
people who watch this all the time
as opposed to the public.
- Exactly.
- Okay, my executive producer
informs me you're Ali Vitali.
I'm Ali Velshi.
- I've heard that, yeah.
- This was the Ali V segment.
Good to see you, my friend.
- You too.
- Joe Biden and Kamala Harris
will pause their fight,
by the way, over past education policy
to talk about the current state
of America's public schools.
They're scheduled to join eight other
Democratic presidential candidates
at the National Education Association's
Strong Public Schools
Presidential Forum in Houston.
The contenders will answer
questions from classroom teachers
and other educational professionals.
MSNBC's Mariana Atencio
joins us now from Houston.
The forum is going to begin
at the top of the hour.
Mariana, some of the
candidates have outlined plans
to improve the education
system, and you've had a chance
to talk with educators
who are at the event.
What are they looking for?
What are the attendees looking for
from the presidential candidates?
- Ali, educators want to
know from the candidates
how they plan to increase
teacher pay, first of all.
We've seen teachers, for the most part,
rally and strike across the country
for increased teacher pay,
but also how the candidates
are going to increase
funding for education, how
they're gonna make educators
stay in the classroom.
Many teachers here tell
me they have to work
two, three jobs just to be an educator,
and they're having to put their own money
toward buying textbooks
and school supplies.
So how these candidates
are gonna improve
conditions in classrooms.
But it also goes beyond education.
I spoke to one teacher named
Christina from Denver, Colorado
who tells me she has a
classroom of mixed status kids,
a lot of Latino families.
So she's also interested to know
about the candidates'
immigration proposals,
because whatever they do on immigration
will inevitably affect
the kids in her classroom.
And then finally, what you
were talking about with Ali V.
A lot of chatter here about
that contested exchange
over race between Biden and Harris.
A lot of educators also
wanna see what both of them
will talk about regarding
that at the forum today.
Ali?
- I appreciate that.
Thank you, my friend, Mariana Atencio.
We're gonna check in with
you a little bit later.
And a quick programming note.
In the next hour, I'm
gonna be talking live
to Senator Amy Klobuchar.
She's one of the 2020 contenders
who is attending today's forum in Houston.
We are going to talk about
her public education policies.
That is three p.m. Eastern
right here on MSNBC.
All right, the President says
ICE agents will soon begin
a nationwide roundup of
undocumented immigrants
and claim border
facilities are clean, fine
and only overcrowded because of Democrats.
Texas Democratic Congressman Marc Veasey,
who toured border facilities,
detention facilities
this week, joins me next.
You're watching MSNBC.
- Choosing to foster a
child is choosing to nurture
and emotionally support
children in urgent need.
It's not just about opening up your home.
It is also about opening up your heart.
Consider fostering.
The more you know.
(stomach grumbles)
♪ When you have nausea,
heartburn, indigestion ♪
♪ Upset stomach, diarrhea ♪
- [Announcer] Try new Pepto Liquicaps
for fast relief and ultra coating.
♪ Nausea, heartburn, indigestion ♪
♪ Upset stomach ♪
- [Announcer] Get powerful relief
with new Pepto Bismol Liquicaps.
- My team spent a lot of
time and money posting jobs.
We would get a flood of resumes,
but finding the right person
was nearly impossible.
My budget has to stretch,
but my time can't.
I was tired of using 12 vendors.
Then I learned that
CareerBuilder has everything,
data to help us plan, a single
source to find candidates,
marketing tools to engage them,
and the fastest background
screening on the market.
So we made the switch.
Now, we get the right person faster.
It's not just efficient.
It's smart.
CareerBuilder, work can work.
- Most homeowners draw a blank
when asked what their
home projects should cost.
That's why at HomeAdvisor, you can see
what others paid for
similar jobs in your area.
Start you next home project
knowing what you should pay.
Go to HomeAdvisor.com or
download the free app.
(phone vibrates)
(alarm beeps)
- [Announcer] This is your wake-up call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis
month after month, the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
Humira can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
Humira targets and blocks
the source of inflammation
that contribute to joint
pain and irreversible damage.
- [Announcer] Humira
can lower your ability
to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes fatal infections
including tuberculosis and cancers,
including lymphoma have happened,
as have blood, liver and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions
and new or worsening heart failure.
Tell your doctor if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB, hepatitis
B, are pone to infections
or have flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start Humira if
you have an infection.
- [Announcer] Help stop the clock
on further irreversible joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here, right now, Humira.
♪ Don't waste your time and
money at the chain store ♪
♪ RockAuto ♪
♪ We got the best auto parts ♪
♪ Brake parts, suspension
parts and dealer parts too ♪
♪ RockAuto ♪
♪ The website so easy to use ♪
♪ The lowest prices
and fast delivery too ♪
♪ All the parts your car will ever need ♪
♪ All the savvy folks are
buying parts at RockAuto.com ♪
♪ All the parts your car will ever need ♪
- [Narrator] The following
is a car warranty alert.
If you're driving without an auto warranty
or it's close to expiring,
you could be at risk
of expensive auto repairs
that could cost you thousands.
CarShield could qualify you
for an auto protection plan
that could save you from
expensive auto repair bills.
Choose the CarShield
plan that's right for you
so you won't have to
pay for covered repairs.
No more worrying if you
can afford a breakdown.
No more expensive parts and labor.
No vehicle inspection.
No credit checks.
Plus you can pick any ASE-certified
mechanic or dealership
to fix your car.
You also receive roadside
assistance, rental car coverage
and hotel reimbursement while traveling.
Breakdowns happen, but you
don't have to get stuck
with expensive repair bills.
Don't put yourself or your wallet at risk.
CarShield cars go farther.
Call CarShield now for
your free instant quote.
Call 800-921-0731.
800-921-0731.
- [Announcer] With a
mattress at Casper.com.
- Well, don't call them raids.
I say they came in illegally,
and we're bringing them out legally.
These are people where we have the papers,
we've gone through the court system.
They'll be starting fairly soon,
but I don't call 'em raids.
Thousands and thousands of
people will be legally removed
from the country, and
that process has started.
And we've actually been
doing that for a long time.
- President Trump announced
he'd be carrying out
his initiative to round up and mass deport
thousands of undocumented migrants
back to their home countries fairly soon.
This comes almost two
weeks after he called of
threatened raids to, "see if
the Democrats and Republicans
"can get together and work
out a solution to the asylum
"and loophole problems
at the southern border."
But a week later at the G20 summit,
he said immigration raids
would likely take place
sometime after the July 4th holiday.
It comes just as more reports
reveal that the administration
has been sending heft fines
of up to nearly $500,000
to migrants who seek refuge
in places of warship.
Joining me now is Democratic
representative from Texas,
Marc Veasey, who traveled
to El Paso to visit
several detention facilities in the area.
Congressman, good to see you.
Thank you for being with us.
- Ali.
- The President has implied
that what congressmen are seeing,
either they're being dishonest about it
or they're not actually seeing.
What have you seen?
And how does that compare
to what other congressmen
have told us, other members
of Congress have told us,
and our own reporters have
seen about overcrowding,
and the shortage of food and
blankest and things like that?
- Right, exactly.
Well, I was on the trip to
El Paso several days ago,
and we visited one of the
detention centers there
that was under a lot of scrutiny.
And what we saw was at
least one holding cell
that was crowded.
And they had Cuban
migrants that were placed
in this particular cell, and they told us
the reason why they were
in such an overcrowded cell
was because the Cubans didn't mix well
with the other people from
Latin American countries.
So they wanted to keep
them together in that cell.
They were crying.
They were sad.
One grandmother told a story
of her mentally impaired grandson
being separated from her.
And they did tell
members of the delegation
that when they asked for water,
that they were told to
drink out of the toilet.
Now, you know, I have to tell you,
based on this Facebook page that came out,
and that story actually broke
while we were on our trip to El Paso,
I believe that the Border Patrol
agents did tell them that.
I absolutely believe that they've
been mean to this people--
- Tell me the connection between the two,
because you know that there
are almost 10,000 people
on this Facebook page
in which it has Customs
and Border Protection
employees and officers
saying disparaging, sexist,
racist, misogynistic things
about both members of
Congress, and migrants,
asylum seekers, even
people crossing the river.
- Right, yes.
I think it's a broader
part of the culture there.
Now, it's actually broken that they have
actually known about this page
perhaps for up to three years,
and they were not surprised about this.
When we got there and we talked
with the Customs and Border Patrol people
that were in charge of
our tour, they told us,
"Oh, my god, we've never heard of this."
But come on, three years?
If that's true, then that
means that we were lied to,
that members of Congress where lied to
on the trip about this page.
And again, the fact that
they would be mean to people
and that there were kids that
were in overcrowded conditions
that were walking around
with mucus-filled shirts,
stories that were told to us,
stories that, in my opinion,
were backed up the the IG's report,
and even the acting Homeland Secretary
said that the conditions
there are not good,
I mean, everything that
I've heard from the migrants
while I was there on my
trip, I 100% believe.
- Congressman, the President
talked about it this morning.
He says members of Congress
are attacking Border Patrol.
Let's listen.
- I've seen some of those places,
and they are run beautifully.
They're clean.
They're good.
They do a great job.
They're crowded because the
Democrats will not give us
any relief from these loopholes.
We have loopholes that are so bad,
we have asylum that's so bad.
I think that the Border
Patrol has been treated
very, very badly by certain
members of Congress,
very, very badly.
For the most part, they're
very respected by Congress,
but certain members of Congress
say very bad things
and lie and exaggerate.
- So what do you have to
say about that, Congressman?
He's saying that certain
members of Congress
lie and exaggerate.
But in fact, this Border Patrol stuff
wasn't actually reported
by members of Congress.
It was reported by somebody in that group
who linked it to ProPublica.
- Yeah, that is absolutely right.
And you know, the President
has never seen a lie
that he didn't like.
And right now, he's just spinning.
He's playing politics
like he's been playing
politics with these migrants.
And absolutely, Ali, everything
that I've heard about
and everything that the President has,
you know, he's trying to almost
like pit the Border Patrol agents
and try to make this a political issue.
But I will tell you that there was another
Border Patrol agent, you
may have saw the interview,
and he even backed up
the deplorable conditions
in which the migrants were living in.
And so I don't see this
as an issue of Democrats
versus Border Patrol agents.
I think that there are some
agents there that feel like,
that they are empowered to do
anything that they wanna do
because of the direction that they get
from the executive branch,
from the statements
that come out of the President's mouth,
from the actions that come out
of the President's
immigration policy people
like Stephen Miller.
I think that that sort of culture
has been allowed to exist there.
But I, by no means, think
that every Border Patrol agent
is a bad person.
We even heard from
lawyers and other people,
before we began our tour
in El Paso, that wanted
to let us know that some of
these Border Patrol agents
are members of the
community in good standing.
We work with them, that they
were part of their families,
and that they certainly
did not paint them with a broad brush.
And I'm not trying to do that right now.
I'm saying that they have a problem there
and it needs to be rooted out.
And I'm very happy that Elijah Cummings
is going to hold a hearing on
oversight and investigation
so we can look into some
of these allegations.
Not just with the Facebook page,
with the overcrowding conditions.
Congressman, good to talk to you.
Thank you for taking
time to discuss with us,
Representative Marc Veasey of Texas.
All right, coming up next,
tensions with Iran go from bad to worse.
This time, it's Tehran and
the UK in the crosshairs
after the British Royal Navy
seized an Iranian oil tanker.
Today, new threats of
retaliation from Iran.
You are watching MSNBC.
- So how are you feeling
on a scale of one to five?
One to five?
It's more like five million.
There's everything from happy,
to extremely happy.
There's also angry.
- Really angry, Clive!
- Actually really angry.
- Thank you.
- But what if your business can understand
what your customers are feeling
and then do something about it?
Turn problems into opportunities.
- Thanks, drone.
- Customers into fanatics.
Change the whole experience.
- All right, who wants to go again?
(passengers chatter)
- I do!
I do!
- [Clive] I have a really
good feeling about this.
- It's quite the buffet
at this hotel, isn't it?
- It really is.
- And so close to the stadium.
I managed to book the
last room for 150 bucks.
- I booked the last
room a few months back.
- Booked the last room a week ago.
- I booked yesterday, one night, $99.
- [Group] What?
- How?
- Some hotel booking sites panic you
into booking the last room,
but they often don't have
all the availability.
Instead, use Trivago.
Trivago will search for available rooms
and compare hotel prices
from hundreds of websites worldwide.
- At least I got the
last ticket to the game.
- [Group] Me too.
- [Announcer] Hotel?
Trivago.
- [Announcer] Important message
for women and men ages 50 to 85.
Right now, in areas like yours,
people have already called
about life insurance through
the Colonial Penn program
and received their free
beneficiary planner.
Have you received your free planner?
If not, I encourage you
to pick up the phone
and take advantage of this free offer.
In addition to your free
beneficiary planner,
you will also receive free information
on affordable whole life insurance
that has a lifetime rate
lock that guarantees
your rate can never
increase for any reason.
If you did not receive your
free beneficiary planner,
call this number now.
Please stand by to learn more.
- I'm Alex Trebek here to tell you
about a popular life insurance
plan with a rate lock
that locks in your rate for
life so it can never increase.
Did you get your free information kit?
If not, please call this number now.
This affordable plan through
the Colonial Penn program
has coverage options
for just $9.95 a month.
Your rate is locked in
and can never go up.
And your acceptance is guaranteed,
with no health questions.
See how much coverage you can
get for just $9.95 a month.
Call now for your free information kit.
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-505-6035
for your free information
and your free beneficiary planning.
There's no obligation.
That number again is 1-800-505-6035.
Call now.
(electronic music)
(plastic crunches)
(group gasps)
♪ You're on the master list ♪
♪ And you aint ever gonna
get up off of the stage ♪
♪ You're gonna be exalted
just like a queen ♪
♪ Get used to this face
don't go fadin' out ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Shine ♪
♪ Brighter than all the others ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Fly ♪
♪ Higher than the stars above you ♪
- With the money I've made on Poshmark,
I've been able to pay for
all our family's vacations.
- I could pay for my wedding
just on what I've made from Poshmark.
- I've made over $10,000,
and I was able to buy my new car.
- [Announcer] Download
the free Poshmark app now.
- [Announcer] Paul, you're
the greatest neighbor.
You help us find the best
home improvement pros,
get quotes and research
prices for our home projects.
- That, that's not me.
That's HomeAdvisor.
- [Announcer] You can't expect
your neighbors to do it all,
so just ask HomeAdvisor.
- Iran has threatened to
seize a British oil tanker
after authorities in Gibraltar
detained an Iranian
oil tanker on Thursday.
The British say the ship
breached European Union sanctions
by carrying a shipment
of crude oil to Syria.
Iranian authorities believe
the British were acting on intelligence
from the United States
when they seized the ship.
The latest incident comes
as Iranian President
Hassan Rouhani said that
his country will begin
enriching Uranium as early as Sunday
to a level that would exceed the limits
specified under the 2015 Nuclear Accord.
Let's bring in NBC's Tehran
Bureau Chief, Ali Arouzi
live from Tehran.
Ali, this is a tricky one
because much of the Syrian regime
despised around the world
and even in the region
is supported by the Iranians,
so it would be logical,
to some people, to think
that Iran is supplying
oil to Syria.
What do we know about what happened here?
- Well, Ali, what we know is
that this was the (mumbles)
that Iran says that they earned.
And it was taking crude oil to Syria,
but it was taking a very
curious route to Syria.
Instead of going through the Suez Canal,
which would be a massive
shortcut for this supertanker
to take, it went around the tip of Africa,
all the way up towards the
Mediterranean coast of Syria,
where it was seized in
Gibraltar by British Marines.
Now, it's very odd that
it would take this route.
Now some people are saying
that this may have been
a smokescreen by the Iranians
to disguise its route
because it's not allowed
to take oil to Syria
because of EU sanctions.
And the British were tipped
off by the United States
that this cargo was heading to Syria,
and some 30 British Marines
then boarded the ship.
They boarded it by ropes
coming down on helicopters,
while others came on speedboats.
And now, the ship is being
held in Gibraltar waters.
The crew of the ship are being questioned.
It's not clear whether
they're being questioned
on land or on the sea.
And incidentally, most of the crew
are Pakistanis and Indians, not Iranians.
They're not being treated as criminals
but rather as witnesses.
Now, the authorities
in Gibraltar have said
that they are gonna keep the
ship for another two weeks
until the investigation comes to an end,
but Iran is obviously up in arms.
They are saying that
this is an act of piracy
by the British, and an Iranian commander,
revolutionary guard commander is saying
that a British oil tanker
should be seized in retaliation.
- All right, Ali Arouzi,
thank you so much,
NBC News Tehran Bureau Chief Ali Arouzi.
The situation with Iran
is just one of several
foreign policy crises
that President Trump is dealing with.
The President is also
trying to reach an agreement
with China to end his trade war
and a deal with North Korea
to curb its nuclear program.
While Democrats and some
Republicans have criticized
the President's handling
of foreign policy issues,
his core supporters still appear
to be onboard with his efforts.
Joining us to take a closer
look at this is Henry Olsen.
Henry is a senior fellow
at the Ethics and Public Policy Center.
He's also an opinion columnist
for The Washington Post,
and he wrote a column on this issue
that was published last week.
Henry, good to see you.
Thank you for being with us.
- Thanks for having me on.
- Henry, I wanna read a
little bit from this column
that you published in which
you say about Donald Trump,
"His fans, not surprisingly,
take a different view.
"Most don't subscribe to the
Trump as Superman fantasy.
"Instead, they recognize that experts
"have been in charge of US
foreign policy for decades
"and, they argue, we have
little to show for it.
"North Korea has nuclear weapons.
"China has emerged as a
dangerous geopolitical foe.
"In their view, Trump's
dramatic breaks with the past
"could be the only chance
the United States has
"to avert dangerous conflicts
with one or both nations.
"Better to take a chance
on him, they reason,
"than hope more of the same
will yield different results."
I think that's a remarkably
sophisticated view
of what might be happening.
Do you think that Donald
Trump's base holds that view
of how he handles foreign affairs?
- I think the President's base
is very supportive of him.
They think he has America's
best interests at heart.
They think that he's
not going to be somebody
who sends American boys and girls to die
for an ally's interest,
that's not immediately
in America's interest.
And I think they are willing
to take some pain or take some risks
in order to confront
Chian and North Korea.
The polls have shown for
years that being critical
towards China is a winner,
particularly in the Midwest
and particularly with eh people who moved
from Democratic to Republican
to support President Trump.
So I think they're supportive of him,
and I think they're willing
to give him a lot of rope
and give them a lot of opportunities
to show that he's doing the right thing.
- So in both of these cases,
a lot of rope has been
been ceded, in fact.
In China, we've been reporting
on farmers who are suffering
because their crop prices are low.
They've been getting
some reimbursements from the government.
But every last farmer we talked to says,
"I'd rather have money from my crops."
Yet, you're right.
When we talked to them,
they say, "We're still
sticking by the President."
When does that run out, that goodwill?
- Well, I think it may
not run out very quickly.
I think you've got people who recognize
that this has been a long time coming.
China ceded to the WTO
almost 20 years ago.
Millions of people have lost their jobs,
according to MIT and University
of San Diego economists,
because of Chinese import competition.
And the fact that some
farmers are losing money,
they can look around and see
that their neighbors lost
a lot more than they did.
So I think that as long
as the President is firm
and as long as the
President is consistent,
that the rope they give
him may be extended
for quite a while longer.
- I mean, these farmers live
on a razor's edge of margins.
Are you saying that it
might be another year or two
that they'll stick by the President?
- I think it depends.
It depends on what the President does.
But the thing to remember is that
the farmers receive a lot
of government support.
They receive revenue support,
the soybean farmers in
particular and corn farmers
are able to buy into a
government-financed insurance program
that guarantees their revenues.
Plus they have a price support program.
Plus they have a disaster program.
This is a group that may prefer
to sell to steady markets
but they have a lot of
support from the government,
plus the temporary support
that the President has been adding
to see them through over
the next couple of years.
- Henry, good to talk to you.
We'll continue this
conversation another time.
We appreciate it.
- Thank you.
- Henry Olsen
is Vice President and Director
at the National Research Initiative.
All right, today, good news
from the monthly jobs report.
200,000 jobs were added,
further proof our economy is strong.
But why doesn't it seem to
be working for everyone?
That is the big question.
You're watching MSNBC.
- [Announcer] Have you ever
seen something so beautiful
that all you could say was, "Wow!"
Beaches Turks & Caicos,
where anything is possible
because everything is included.
Wow.
Get up to 65% off.
Call 1-800-Beaches.
- I have one kid in each
branch of the military,
but I'm command central.
- [Announcer] Why Elaine chose Verizon.
- It's so important to us
that Verizon is supporting
military families.
When I have a child deployed,
having a reliable
network means everything.
So when I get a video chat
and I get to see their face,
it's the best thing in the world.
And I've earned every
one of these gray hairs.
Military moms, we serve too.
- [Announcer] The network
more people rely on
gives you more,
like military plans with a
special price on unlimited,
$100 per line, and big savings
on our best phones when you switch.
That's Verizon.
- When I book at hilton.com,
I get to select my room
from the floor plan,
free Wi-Fi, and a price match guarantee.
- So with Hilton, there is no catch.
- Yeah, the only catch is
I'm never leaving. (chuckles)
No, I'm serious.
I live here now.
Book at hilton.com and get the
Hilton price match guarantee.
- No, wrong move.
Old-fashioned bandages get dirty.
They can let in water and germs.
Look, it's falling off.
New-Skin is the flexible liquid bandage
that seals out the bad stuff.
There's a spray too.
- [Announcer] New-Skin,
rethink how you heal.
- It's so easy to sell on Poshmark.
You just pick out your item,
snap a couple of photos,
and boom, it's up for sale.
When I look at my old clothes
now, I see dollar signs
just this month, I made a
couple of hundred dollars
on Poshmark just selling
items out of my closet.
- [Announcer] Download
the free Poshmark app now.
- The United States is
in its longest period
of economic expansion on record,
but there is a widening gap
between the richest
Americans and everyone else.
Now much of that has to do
with wealth and the ability
for the middle class of
America to attain it.
Let's just discuss what this is.
Wealth are your assets.
I think everybody knows this, your home,
your durable goods like your
TVs, your refrigerators,
any stocks you own, pension
plans, if you own a business.
All that minus your liabilities,
things like your mortgage,
credit card debt,
car payments, things like
that, that's your wealth,
your assets minus your
liabilities, your balance sheet.
More than a third of
gains in household wealth
went to the wealthiest
1% over the past decade.
This actually goes all the way to 1989.
And you can see the top 1%
here and the bottom 50% here
were in unison until the mid '90s.
Remember, that's when China
joined the World Trade Organization.
We started buying more stuff from them.
Globalization and technology took hold.
And you start to see what that did.
The top 1% ended up with these gains.
The chart shows the fourth
quarter total net worth
of the top 1% of wealth
holders and the bottom 50%.
These figures, by the way,
are in millions of dollars.
As you can see, the bottom 50%
barely, barely making any gains at all.
In fact, for a little
while here in the 2000s,
they were making negative gains.
They were losing wealth.
Okay, what's causing
this dramatic disparity?
The Associated Press analyzed
that few middle class owners
or fewer middle class
Americans are owning homes.
The price gains if you own a
home has made home ownership
less feasible for new buyers.
So if you had a home, you've done well.
If you didn't have a home,
the prices have made it hard to get in.
But then the recession occurred
and nearly eight million
Americans lost their homes.
Since then, prices have
again risen dramatically
in places like wealthy metro areas,
especially along the coast.
In 2004, middle class home ownership rates
stood at about 70%.
In 2016, we're now at about 60%.
So that's one area of wealth.
There's also the issue
of low participation
in the stock market.
We talk a lot about the stock market.
The President talks a lot
about the stock market.
But the proportion of
middle income household
that own shares has actually declined.
In 2007, 56% of middle class
Americans owned shares.
And by the way, in 2016,
that dropped to 50%.
This decline is attributed
to more middle income workers
taking jobs that don't have
retirement savings plans,
as well as expenses like
healthcare and student loan debt
which are taking those bills, that money
that would have gone to investment.
Now compare that investment
rate to the top 10%.
Almost everybody in
the top 10% owns stock.
In 2007, the number was 93%.
It is up to 95% in 2016.
So this is wealth disparity.
Joining me now is Washington Post
economics correspondent Heather Long.
Her recent op ed speaks
directly to this issue.
And Heather, the simple question
here is that in shorthand,
if Martians came down to Earth and said,
"How is your economy doing,"
the short answer would have to be good.
And only if they ask a second question
would you be able to say,
"But it is really not evenly distributed."
- I think you're right.
As I traveled the country,
that's exactly what I hear.
Americans will tell you
that this is definitely
a better economy than
it was in 2008, in '09
during the great
recession, but the next but
out of their mouths is they
still feel a lot of anxiety.
And in our story today, we call it
40% of Americans are still
struggling to pay their bills
which seems like a very
unusually high statistic
in a moment when we have
such a low employment rate,
and the President keeps talking about
a blue collar jobs boom.
So why do we still have
this bottom 40% that's
still hurting so much.
And there's really two parts to it.
You just walkED through the wealth so well
people don't have as much of
a cushion as they did before.
We have half the population
that has still not recovered
the level of wealth that they had
just before the great recession.
So they still don't have
as much of a cushion
as what they would like
to have in a normal time,
let alone heading into
any potential downturn.
- And we know that
statistically, but in your piece,
you actually wrote about
that very specifically.
I'm reading from your piece.
It says, "In discussions with
30 Americans unable to pay
"all of their bills, a
clear pattern emerged.
"Most were able to eke by until they faced
"an unexpected crisis,
such as a job loss, cancer,
"car trouble, or storm damage."
Or in the case of this year,
we saw with government
employees who were furloughed
or when the government shut down.
These are middle income workers.
These are not poor Americans.
But some setback will set them off,
and that means they are constantly living
with a level of anxiety
which will cause them to say,
"I'm not sure whose great
economy you're talking about
"because I'm scared every month."
- Yeah, that's exactly right.
I think what we've really
learned in the last decade
about people who are in the working class
is how volatile their situations are.
There's a lot less certainty
around the hours you're going to work
and how much you're going
to make during those hours.
Retail workers have talked
a lot about how frustrated
they are about not knowing
their schedule week to week.
And on the flip side is
that people not having
that cushion anymore, they
haven't been able to save.
They haven't been able,
after losing homes,
to get back on that
housing or stock market,
to build back up their
savings and their assets
to weather a rainy day situation.
It's pretty stunning.
I think the Kaiser Foundation
group that studies healthcare
had a pretty incredible statistic.
It's something like one in six Americans,
even if they have health insurance,
will face an unexpectedly large bill
that they hadn't planned for every year.
- Heather, good to talk to you.
Thank you for the story
that you've written.
We'll continue to have this conversation,
because I think it's the most important
economic conversation of our time.
Heather Long is a Washington
Post economics correspondent.
Another quick reminder, in a few minutes,
at the top of the hour,
I'm gonna speak live
to 2020 contender Senator Amy Klobuchar,
one of the many Democratic
candidates speaking today
at an educational forum in Houston.
sTick around.
You don't wanna miss that conversation
in just a few minutes.
You are watching MSNBC.
(laid back music)
- [Announcer] Nothing
feels like connecting
with the people that matter.
Holiday Inn, Holiday Inn Express.
We're there so you can be too.
- [Announcer] It all comes down
to a single defining moment,
when a plan stops being a
plan and gets set into motion.
Today's Merrill can help you get there
with the people, tools
and personalized advice
to help turn your ambitions into action.
What would you like the power to do?
- What makes Creative Planning
different from other financial advisers?
aS an independent firm with
over $40 billion in assets,
We have the experience that you deserve.
And our advisers are always fiduciaries,
legally bound to act
in your best interest.
And rather than mange your investments
based solely on age OR risk tolerance,
we consider your entire financial picture,
including tax and legal plaNning,
to create a complete plan
that's right for you.
So call 866-Creative and
experience the difference.
Creative planning.
- [Announcer] Men, wanna feel
younger, stronger, leaner?
You don't have to slow down after 40.
Frank Thomas found the
secret to staying in shape
with the energy and drive of his 20s.
- Man, you look like you
could still hit it a mile.
- I feel great too.
- What gives?
- After 40, men slow down.
It's harder to stay in shape.
- Why?
- Our free testosterone levels drop.
It happened to me.
And then I found Nugenix Total-T.
- [Announcer] New Nugenix
Total-T is our most powerful
man-boosting formula
ever, because it boosts
your free testosterone and
your total testosterone.
Nugenix Total-T helps provide
even more energy,
performance, testosterone,
and muscle boosting ingredients
for even better results.
To get your complimentary
bottle of Nugenix Total-T,
text LEAN to 231 231.
Samples are not available in stores.
- Why wait when you can
do something about it now?
- I gotta try Nugenix Total-T.
- [Announcer] Text LEAN to 231231 now
for your complementary
bottle of Nugenix Total-T.
That's L-E-A-N to 231231.
- [Announcer] And stop
overpaying for car insurance.
- All right, it looks like
the longest economic expansion
in US history is going to continue
at least for the time being.
The Labor Department reported
today that hiring rebounded
in June with employers adding
224,000 new jobs last month.
That's up from just 72,000 in May,
which was a not very good number.
The unemployment rate ticked up to 3.7%.
That's a sign that more people
are returning to the workforce.
And average hourly earnings were up
just over 3% year over year.
President Trump hailed the
news as he left the White House
to spend the weekend at
his New Jersey golf club.
- We had great numbers this morning.
I think it was 224,000 jobs.
Those were really unexpectedly good.
And our country continues
to do really well,
really, really well, so
we're very happy about it.
- President Trump may
be happy about the news.
The markets don't seem to care as much.
Taking a look at the big board,
we have now at least moved to the point
where we're kind of flat.
The problem here, of course,
is that a strong jobs number
means that the Fed may
not lower interest rates,
which is something the Fed
doesn't really seem to wanna do,
but the President really,
really wants the Fed to do.
And that's why that's troubling
investors a little bit.
But again, it's a holiday trading day.
I wouldn't put too much stock
into anything you see in the market.
We've got mixed performance.
We've got the NASDAQ up, and
the Dow and the S&P down.
Let's take a closer look at
this with Michael Strain.
He's the director of
economic policy studies
and a resident scholar at the
American Enterprise Institute.
We would call him a
conservative economist.
Michael, good to see you, my friend.
This is a tricky situation
for the President
because he loves a strong stock market
and he loves low job
numbers, and he's got both
at the moment but he wants the
Fed to lower interest rates.
Is that something that that
just gives the Fed pause?
- Yeah, I think it does
give the Fed pause.
I think that there's
generally been a lot of hype
about the path of interest rates
among commentators and on Wall Street.
Before today's job numbers, you know,
talk of a 50-basis-point
cut or something like that.
I think the Fed,
well, a lot of the concern about
the slowness of the economy
was based on what we saw
in last month's job number,
when it was reported that the
economy added 75,000 jobs.
People were concerned that that
was a market turning point,
that the economy was slowing,
and perhaps slowing rapidly,
and the Fed needed to get
out ahead of the economy
and kind of cushion the blow.
Today, we see a totally different story.
And I think people overreacted
to last month's news.
It's important not to
overreact to this month's news.
What I think we're seeing is an economy
adding about 150 to 180,000 jobs a month,
slower than in 2018 but
still solid and still steady.
- You wrote an oped for
The Guardian newspaper
in which you talked about
how with the economy
being in as good a shape
as the data suggests,
it's a strange time to debate
whether capitalism is broken.
And I think you and I have
had this conversation before.
It's a conversation I just
had with Heather Long.
The remarkable wealth
inequality in the United States
and basically around the world
is what's making people say,
"Hey, I see the stock market
going up all the time.
"I see home prices going up all the time.
"I see the strong economy, but my wages,"
particularly for some.
Maybe it's about a third of Americans,
they feel left out of this whole thing.
About a similar percentage of
people in the United Kingdom
feel left out of it, people
in France, people in Germany.
The Arab Spring started
with something very similar
where people said, "I'm
doing what society said
"I was supposed to do,
and I'm not partaking
"of the fruits of this
remarkable economic growth."
- Yeah, you know, as I look
into the numbers more and more,
I'm less and less convinced
that inequality is
actually the story here.
If you look from say 1980
until the great recession,
you see a significant
increase in inequality.
If you look over the last 10 years,
inequality growth has actually flattened,
and it may have even declined
depending on which income
measure you're interested in.
At the same time as inequality
was soaring during the 1990s,
people weren't concerned about inequality.
So I think people actually care about
how they're doing and--
- Right, right, right.
So in the '90s, so one of the differences
was if everybody's sort
of going up at a level,
in hindsight, when we see those numbers,
I don't know if my control
room has the same numbers
that I put up with Heather Long.
If you see over, since
the '80s and the '90s,
when you've got relative, a flatness
and sometimes even decline
amongst the bottom 50%,
that doesn't feel like
you're doing better.
- Yeah, that's right.
And when we had this massive
crisis, this serious recession,
and then we had a recovery that was slow,
that's typical following
recessions as severe as this one.
But for years and years and years,
we had slow and
non-accelerating wage growth.
- [Ali] Right.
- And over the last few years,
that's changed, thank goodness.
And my sense is that if we
have a long enough period
where wages for typical workers
are growing at a decent clip,
that some of this concern that
we're seeing will die down.
- I hear your argument.
Are you worried that given how long
we're into this expansion
that just by natural causes,
it will slow down
and we won't get that
continued wage growth?
Because it's only really since about 2015
that we've seen a nice bump.
We've seen some of that extra
capacity in the labor market
go away and people are
actually getting raises.
- Yeah, I am worried about
that, and that actually
ties in nicely with what
we learned this morning.
You know, again, a solid month.
But it seems clear that
2019 is going to be
a slower year for the
labor market than 2018.
You know, one of the reasons
is because we're just
running out of workers
to bring in off the sidelines.
We saw the labor force participation rate
tick up this month, that's fantastic,
but there's really only
so high that it can go.
There are only so many
workers we can bring back in.
And at some point, we are
gonna have another recession.
And so I think, you know,
the question is a good one.
How long can we keep
solid wage gains going?
And if the answer is not that much longer,
then what does that do
to kind of politics,
and what does that do
to popular sentiment?
I think that's an important
question we're facing.
- Michael, I always enjoy talking to you.
Thank you for taking time for us today.
Michael Strain is a resident scholar
at the American Enterprise Institute.
And once again, it remains
unclear if the 2020 census
will include a citizenship question.
Just the last hour,
Justice Department lawyers
told a federal court in
Maryland that they will continue
to look for ways to get
the question on the census
despite an unfavorable ruling
from the Supreme Court.
And the President
reaffirmed his commitment
to including the question
on the census earlier today
maybe by using an executive order.
- I just spoke with the Attorney General.
We have a number of different avenues.
We can use all of them or one.
We're doing very well on that issue.
We're spending $15 to
$20 billion on a census.
We're doing everything.
We're finding out
everything about everybody.
Think of it.
$15 to $20 billion and you're
not allowed to ask 'em,
"Are you a citizen?"
And by the way, if you look
at the history of our country,
it's almost always been asked.
We're fighting very hard against a system
that's a very difficult system,
but we'll make a decision.
- Joining me now is NBC News
justice correspondent, Pete Williams.
Well, that was a moment of
self-awareness for the President
and he say we're fighting in a system,
and it's a very difficult system.
It is complex, and it is difficult.
The President can't actually just say,
"Put the question on now."
- Well, he can, but whether
that will make a difference
remains to be seen.
I think at this point, anything
the administration does
from hereon is going to invite litigation,
and the Justice Department
admitted as such
or conceded the point today in its filing.
This is in Maryland.
This is a separate case.
This is not the one that
went to the Supreme Court.
It's one that is still going on
and which challengers
say adding this question
would be unfair
discrimination and violating
the equal protection
clause of the Constitution.
And what the government says
in the filing before that judge
is that they've been asked to reevaluate
all available options that would allow
for putting this question
back on the census form.
No great surprise there
given what the President
had said this morning.
But they do say that if, for example,
Commerce Secretary Ross comes
up with a new explanation
for wanting to put this
question on the form,
then the plaintiffs, the people
who have challenged that,
would be fully entitled
to challenge the decision at that time.
So they can see that almost
anything they do at this point
will be producing a new lawsuit.
And of course, the issue there
is it puts additional
pressure on the Census Bureau.
The longer these lawsuits
play out in court,
the less time the Census Bureau has
to get these forms printed.
And this letter does say despite
all of this back and forth,
no census forms are being printed now
that have the citizenship
question on them.
They say they are currently enjoined
by all these court rulings
from putting the census questionnaire,
printing, rather, the census questionnaire
that includes the citizenship question.
So they're still trying
to find some way to do it,
but just about anything they try to do
is undoubtedly gonna
produce another lawsuit,
more litigation and more delay.
- For time and logistics
purposes, under what constraints
is the Census Bureau operating?
In other words,
the President talked
about delaying the census.
Is that another court case?
Or can the President actually do that?
- Ah, well, two things.
When he talked about delaying the census,
my sense is that he didn't
really mean putting off
when the doors get knocked on
and when people fill out the form.
Traditionally, the census has
been a snapshot of who's where
on April 1st of every
year that ends in a zero.
And I can't imagine that
that will be delayed.
What I suspect he was talking about
is getting the forms printed.
But the government has
said we have to start
printing these things July
1st, and indeed, they did,
to get them all done in time.
It raises the question though,
if they hae to start over,
if they somehow prevail and
are able to add this question,
could they trash all the stuff
they printed so far and start over?
Will they have enough time?
And I guess the answer is if
they had enough money, yes.
They just get more printers involved
and could probably get it done.
I'm just not sure where
that money comes from,
whether they would have
to go back to Congress,
and that would add
another bit of delay here.
- Pete Williams, never been stumped
by a complicated question.
We appreciate it, my friend.
- Or pretend not to be.
- NBC News justice correspondent,
our good friend, Pete Williams.
With me now, Washington Post
opinion writer, Jennifer Rubin.
She's also an MSNBC political contributor,
and she's a Conservative.
And she writes in a new
headline, Census: A flat-out win
for progressives, the courts and America.
Tell me about that, Jennifer.
Why do you add progressives in that title?
Why do you think it's
a win for progressives?
- I think it's a win for everyone.
I think the progressive groups
that were litigating this,
groups like the ACLU, were
making the very cogent argument
that the President was
including this question
as a way of deterring
people who might be afraid
to give out their information
or the information
of people living with them
regarding their immigrant status
and that this is actually contrary to law.
It's been decided a while back
that the census is supposed
to be capturing everybody.
And by including this question,
you're purposefully diminishing the count
in areas that there probably are gonna be
some blue representatives,
urban areas, for example.
So I think for them,
this was a legal victory
at the Supreme Court.
And now, the President is
kind of playing with words,
and the poor Justice Department
lawyers are having to go
into court to make themselves
look awfully foolish.
Understand what they've said.
They've said, "Well, we
don't have the real reason.
"We don't have the real
non (mumbles) reason yet,
"but give us a few weeks
"and we'll come up with a real reason."
This is absurd.
They're obviously just
looking for another lie.
And to make matters worse,
the Maryland case is the case
in which some new evidence
has come to light,
and this is damning
for the administration.
Apparently, a computer file was discovered
by the daughter of a gentleman
who is designing this
in order to benefit the Republican party,
by over counting, or if you
will, tipping the scales
toward the white population.
This is completely illegal.
This is exactly what the
plaintiffs have been fearing.
And if they wanna go forward,
the plaintiffs are saying,
"Well, yes, let's go forward.
"Let's cover all this new information."
The government filing
today unbelievably said,
"Give us some more time
to think of a reason
"but don't let them look at the
discovery in front of them."
- When you look at the
concept of a census,
it's in the Old Testament, right?
- Right.
- I mean, it has been
historically understood
that if you don't count
properly, you mess up
on the provision of
services to your country.
Should this even be partisan?
Should this be a progressive win?
Shouldn't we just all agree?
And you know, sometimes it's
gonna benefit Conservatives,
and sometimes it's gonna
benefit progressives,
but shouldn't we just
all be counting properly
and not be debating this?
- We should, but unfortunately,
the President has made it partisan.
He is determined not to count everybody
or to set up a question that is designed
to make a count really inaccurate.
He's the only President
that has done this.
He's the only President who has taken
objectively neutral
things that shouldn't be
a matter of non-partisanship--
- [Ali] Right, counting how many people
are in your country--
- Whether it's the Fourth
of July or accounting.
- Counting how many people we are
should be objectively neutral.
- It should be, but not
under this president.
And he was the one who
came up with the idea.
The Secretary of Commerce was the one
who came up with a false reason.
The Chief Justice was very
nice not calling him a liar,
but he essentially said the
reason doesn't match the facts.
That's lying in my book.
But he sent them back to
figure this whole thing out,
I think hoping that it wouldn't come back.
I suspect if it ever comes
back to the Supreme Court,
the Supreme Court will have
used up their patience on this
and will swat it away again.
- What a remarkable,
I mean, of all the things I didn't think
I'd actually be disgusting
as a journalist,
this is just one more
to pile on to the top.
Jennifer, good to see you as always.
Thank you for joining us.
- You too.
- MSNBC political contributor, Jen Rubin.
Up next, you hear it a lot
from the 2020 Democratic
presidential candidates.
They want to invest in education.
Most of them don't have
a very detailed plan
on how they'd do it,
but Senator Amy Klobuchar
just unveiled hers.
I'm gonna talk to her about it
in just a couple of minutes.
And later, the President said he'd start
a big deportation push
after the Fourth of July.
I'll talk to a former ICE chief
about what goes into nationwide
immigration raids next.
You're watching MSNBC.
- And right.
♪ I want it all ♪
- Spicy tuna roll.
- Sushi!
- [Troy] Sashimi combo.
♪ I want it all ♪
(Troy grunts)
- [Announcer] With the
Grubhub delivery app,
if you want it all--
- Delivery for Troy.
- [Announcer] You can
get it all at Grubhub.
Restaurants you love, delivered.
- When you book at Hilton.com,
you get the price match guarantee.
So if you find your room at
a lower rate, Hilton is like,
"We're gonna match that rate
and give you an extra 25% off."
- What would travel sites do
if you found a different price?
- That's not our problem.
It's your problem.
Book at Hilton.com and get the
Hilton price match guarantee.
- Most homeowners draw a blank
when asked what their
home projects should cost.
That's why at HomeAdvisor, you can see
what others paid for
similar jobs in your area.
Start you next home project
knowing what you should pay.
Go to HomeAdvisor.com or
download the free app.
- With the money I've made on Poshmark,
I've been able to pay for
all our family's vacations.
- I could pay for my wedding
just on what I've made from Poshmark.
- I've made over $10,000,
and I was able to buy my new car.
- [Announcer] Download
the free Poshmark app now.
(electronic music)
(plastic crunches)
(group gasps)
♪ You're on the master list ♪
♪ And you aint ever gonna
get up off of the stage ♪
♪ You're gonna be exalted
just like a queen ♪
♪ Get used to this face
don't go fadin' out ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Shine ♪
♪ Brighter than all the others ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Fly ♪
♪ Higher than the stars above you ♪
- [Announcer] Constipation
can happen all around us.
You just need to know where to look.
It can happen where people drive.
It can happen where people play.
It can happen where people exercise.
Constipation can even
happen where people work.
And it happens to all of us.
Luckily, there's Colace,
for gentle relief of
occasional constipation.
It's the number one doctor-recommended
stool softener brand.
- Have you been told you
can't get high-speed internet
where you live?
Well, you can with HughesNet Gen5.
Experience the power of next-generation
satellite internet wherever you live.
HughesNet Gen5 is fast.
You'll get 25 megabits per
second plus built-in Wi-Fi,
and there's no hard data limits.
So wherever you live, now you can do
more of everything you love online,
connect on social media, stay informed,
watch the latest videos, and
help your kids get ahead.
No wonder HughesNet is
America's number one choice
for satellite internet.
- [Announcer] Act now to save big
with our limited time offer.
Get free standard installation
by calling right now.
- So what are you waiting for?
Get HughesNet Gen5.
- [Announcer] To order,
call 1-800-743-9610.
Be sure to ask about our
home phone service too.
Call 1-800-743-9610 today.
- [Announcer] 747474.
- How do you learn how to
run when you've never done
anything remotely like this before?
- We're prepared to do it in a novel way,
in an original way.
And we wanna make sure that
we're writing our own playbook.
- Do you think that we should
keep troops in Afghanistan?
- I do not, and I believe
that we need to do it
though in a responsible way.
- Where do you see your party right now?
- It's going to be how do we
think government should work
and who do we think
government should work for.
- The parades, picnics and
other July 4th events are over,
and the Democratic presidential candidates
have returned to serious
policy discussions.
Today, a number of them are
talking about education.
10 Democratic contenders are taking part
in the National Education Association's
Strong Public Schools Presidential Forum
taking place right now in Houston.
Bernie Sanders, you can
see up there on the stage.
One of the candidates
participating in today's event
is Minnesota senator Amy Klobuchar
whose mother was a second grade teacher.
A short time ago, she
unveiled a new proposal
called progress partnerships,
a federal state effort to provide
additional resources and
funding for public schools.
In order to take part,
states will need to do
or have already done the following things.
With regard to teacher pay,
states will agree to a
state federal partnership
that includes generous federal matches
to increase salaries for all teachers.
States will also have
to work with educators
to develop and submit recommendations
on how schools can meet the
needs of working families
like after-school programs,
alternative programs
and community schools.
The plan also calls for
generous federal funding
to improve school infrastructure.
States will also have
to create a mechanism
for distributing those
funds that make sure
to address disparities in
conditions and resources
and provide equal funding for
districts across the state.
And states will also need
to convene a commission
to review their existing
education funding formula
to ensure that all students,
particularly those with
the greatest needs,
have access to adequate
educational resources.
Senator Klobuchar joins me now
from the NEA conference in Houston.
She is a contender for
the presidency in 2020.
Senator, good to see you again.
Thank you for being with us.
- Well, thanks, Ali.
Thanks for mentioning my mom.
She would have loved to be here today.
She taught second grade
until she was 70 years old.
- [Ali] Wow.
- And I still have people come up to me
and say she was their favorite teacher.
Her favorite unit she taught
was the monarch butterfly one
where she would dress up as
a butterfly with antennas,
tights, and carry a sign
that said to Mexico or bust.
- [Ali] That is amazing.
- [Amy] Because that's where
the monarch butterflies flew.
- [Ali] We've got a picture of
her on the screen, actually.
- She was an incredible teacher.
And there she is, yes.
And she actually, she was
the teacher of the year
for her district a number of times.
And one of the things that she
thought very strongly about
was that all kids, which
I have now inherited,
all kids deserve a right
to a good education.
And that's why I went to public school.
My daughter went to public schools,
including a number of years in a school
that was nearly 90%
free and reduced lunch.
So I have a sense of
what's going on there,
and I can tell you right
now, there should be
more federal investment and
more focus on education.
If we wanna participate
in this global economy,
our kids have to be able to do a good job.
And to do a good job,
you need good teachers.
And to recruit good teachers,
you need to have good pay,
and you need to make sure that
the kids are getting prepared
for the jobs we have available today.
- So we have 330 million in
the United States, roughly.
We have 50 million public
school students in 2017.
And fundamentally, the responsibility
for educating those students
falls to the states.
So while I'm deeply appreciative
of the thought that goes
into plans like yours
and the other candidates,
states, in general,
have been underfunding, very deliberately
underfunding public
education for decades now.
We have created a world in
which people like your mother
are not treated the way they should be
in terms of the respect and
the pay they should be given.
Teachers now, public school
teachers who may earn
whatever they earn are often taking money
out of their own pockets to
buy supplies for their schools.
How do you
shift that conversation?
- Exactly, my mom did that.
- Because the federal
government can't take
all that responsibility.
- My mom did that.
Okay, so the federal
government is spending
like 3% of education costs,
and you should move that up.
And let me tell you, exactly what you said
is why I put these progress
partnerships forward.
I think you need to incentivize
the states to do more,
especially when it comes to teacher pay
and infrastructure, those things.
And you do it with
generous matching grants
and to make sure they're
headed in the right direction.
The second thing, and this is a plan
a number of us have put
forward, Kamala Harris, others,
about increasing teacher pay.
And one of the ways you can
do this is by paying for it
with going back to the numbers
on the estate tax that we had
during the Obama administration
or somewhere around that.
And that would literally
raise enough money
to substantially increase teacher pay.
We're talking here about
that estate tax exemption.
That would be something
that would be really helpful
to recruiting, and that's
federal money, right?
Then you have ideas like mine
which is to incentivize states
to be focusing more on
teachers and our schools
and making sure that we have
more quality in our schools.
That's the way you do it.
- So we have two different
issues that we're dealing with.
One is teacher pay.
And I just wanna show our views.
According to the National
Education Association
hosting the event you're at,
the highest teacher salaries
are in New York, California
and Massachusetts,
upward of $80,000 a year.
The lowest, in Mississippi,
West Virginia and Oklahoma,
in the 40s.
So we've got that problem
that you and I discussed,
and then we've got this other issue,
and that is states with
the highest and lowest
average spending per capital on students.
Again, New York, Washington
state and New Jersey
spent upward of $20,000 per pupil.
Idaho, Utah and Arizona are spending
six, seven and $8,000 per pupil.
We're not even, we're nowhere close
to having a standardized
level of education
if you Look at it through
funding in this country.
- Right, and so that is why,
right, and so that is why
upping the federal role,
putting in an Education
Secretary who is not Betsy DeVos,
making sure that we have
policymakers in place
that understand what education
means and how important it is
for individual families
but also for the future of our country
when we're trying to
compete in a global economy.
And then I think one
really interesting issue
was apprenticeships and doing
more with community colleges
at the high school level.
So that's a lot about
what we are gonna be talking about today.
And I can tell you, school,
college, those are things
that people brought to bring
in the parades and things
that I did the last few days.
I think I'm the only candidate that went,
the last three days,
I've been in Iowa, New
Hampshire and Houston.
People bring up school a lot.
That is core to their families.
And as someone that
didn't come from money,
that stands here today as
a candidate for president
after being the granddaughter
of an iron ore miner
who couldn't finish high school
so he could raise his family,
and the daughter of a teacher
and a newspaper man, I
can speak, walk the walk
when it comes to the
importance of education,
and that's what I'm going to be
talking about today on that stage.
- Senator, one of the other topics
that we cover very closely on this show
is the issue of data privacy
and management with Facebook.
Roger McNamee, who's a
great friend of our show,
talks very fondly of the fact that you,
you don't get a lot of press for this,
but you put a lot of thinking
into how to deal with
Silicon Valley and tech.
Give us a bit of your
idea about how you deal
with the very pressing
and almost daily concerns
that we're hearing about
how these companies operate
and manage our information.
- I think they thought they
could just run the tables
and no one would care because
they're successful companies.
I don't like to take
success away from them.
That's great.
But the point is we need
a counterbalance here.
And the first thing we need
is privacy rules in place.
And they've been able to say,
"Hey, we're just a forum."
No, they're not.
They are media companies.
They've made tons of money off
of individuals' information.
So that's why this idea of
putting privacy rules in place
at one of the few bipartisan
bills out there to do it,
with getting notice of data breaches
and making sure that
there are rules in place
so people can protect their
private data is first.
You also have to make sure
that when they're sharing data,
that there's rules about that.
And I would suggest that
they have to pay a fee, a tax
so that money can go back
into our nation's
cybersecurity to protect us.
And the third thing is
all about democracy.
If we don't do something about this
before the next election,
when we have a president
sending out doctored
videos of Speaker Pelosi,
she's strong, she's gonna
be able to protect herself,
but if this is what our
campaigns are gonna come to,
videos where you can't even
tell if it's the person or not,
we have a major problem.
So making those companies
put some rules of the road
in place when it comes
to who's buying ads,
who is paying for those
ads, what those ads are
so other campaigns and
the media can see them
is gonna be critical.
Why should your network
have to follow those rules
and then these other
billion-dollar companies don't?
It makes no sense at all.
And as we know from 2016,
it played a major role
in spreading fake news and
also allowing, basically,
for foreign countries to have
influence on our election.
And when I heard the President
make a joke about meddling
when he was at the G20,
that's just what we're
dealing with right now.
We're in July 4th week.
We know that millions
of people sacrificed,
serving our country.
Hundreds and thousands of them are dying
That's what's happened, and
yet, he makes a joke about it.
It's not a joke, not to
those who have served
to protect our freedom.
- Senator, I wanna ask
you one last question.
You're from Minnesota,
and you are on the Agriculture Committee.
Just in the last hour, I spoke
to a Conservative economist
who said that while farmers are suffering,
particularly for the price
of their corn or soybeans
because of the trade war,
the amount of subsidy
they get from the federal
government allows them
to justify continuing
to support the President
in these trade wars.
What's your take on that?
- My take is that the farmers I know,
they just wanna make a living.
And they know very well,
the more their soybeans sit at their farms
or they are unable to
sell goods to market,
the more those contracts
are going to farmers
in other countries and foreign lands,
and it's gonna be harder and harder.
They can't just get those
contracts back in a month
so their long-term viability,
we have had more and
more farm bankruptcies,
especially for the small farmers.
So my focus as a senior member
of the Agriculture Committee
and my focus as president
will be to make sure
that we keep our food supply in America.
We do that with a special
focus on our small farmers.
I have a very strong track
record of making sure
these payments aren't going
to the Beverly Hills 90210 area code,
that they're going instead
to our small farmers,
and then making sure that if
we're gonna push on trade,
which we should do, that
we're not using a meat cleaver
like this president has done,
or we can call it a tweet cleaver,
but instead, we're focused
on targeted tariffs
and targeted trade policies
that are really gonna make a difference.
And that's what I'm concerned about
that's going on in the Midwest.
I'm someone that's won in
those red districts, Ali.
I have won in 42 of the counties
that Trump won in my state.
I think that farmers wanna
make a decent living,
and they want someone that
can look them in the eye
and tell them the truth.
They don't always agree with
it, but tell them the truth.
That's something that this
president really does.
- Senator Amy Klobuchar,
thank you for taking
time to talk to us today.
- It was great to be on.
Thank you.
- Amy Klobuchar,
candidate for president,
and she's a senator from Minnesota.
Still ahead, the President
promised to crack down
on illegal immigration
after the Fourth of July.
The holiday's come and gone,
and Trump says the raids will start soon.
I'll talk to a former head of ICE next.
- A major story broke late last night.
- Well, let's start with
the morning's top stories.
- We begin with new data this morning.
- [Announcer] Wake up
with the news you need
to start your day.
Join Amin Mohadin and Yasmin Vossoughian.
- This is your morning rundown.
- [Announcer] First Look,
weekday mornings at five on MSNBC.
- Budget meeting.
- Sweet.
- If you compare last
quarter to this quarter--
- [Group] Mmm.
- [Announcer] It's no
wonder everything seems
a little better with the
creamy taste of Philly.
Made with fresh milk and real cream.
It must be the Philly.
- Shaving has been difficult for me.
I have very sensitive skin.
I get ingrown hairs.
It just stopped that irritation,
that burn that I get.
- I wouldn't use anything else.
- Going to the Shawn
Mendes Verizon Up concert
was like an out-of-body experience.
- [Announcer] Why the Yousafzai
sisters chose Verizon.
- We were right in front of him.
- Dead center, front row.
Actually, Zamila, you
touched Shawn Mendes.
- She touched Shawn Mendes.
- Yeah, I touched him.
He like held my hand for a while,
and then we got to meet
him after, which was like--
- Another surprise.
- Yeah.
We love Verizon even more now.
I'll never forget that day ever.
- [Announcer] The network
more people rely on
gives you more, like thousands of tickets
to concerts, festivals and private shows,
and big savings on our best
phones when you switch.
That's Verizon.
- It's so easy to sell on Poshmark.
You just pick out your item,
snap a couple of photos,
and boom, it's up for sale.
When I look at my old clothes
now, I see dollar signs
just this month, I made a
couple of hundred dollars
on Poshmark just selling
items out of my closet.
- [Announcer] Download
the free Poshmark app now.
- Pain thinks it makes the rules,
but the rules just changed.
New IcyHot lidocaine dry
spray, instant dry technology.
No mess, no residue, fast-acting relief.
Dries your pain.
New IcyHot lidocaine dry spray.
- [Announcer] Too many people in pain
settle for a restless night's sleep.
There's a better choice.
Aleve PM, the only one to
combine a safe sleep aid
and the 12-hour pain-relieving
strength of Aleve
that dares to last into the
morning so you feel refreshed.
Aleve PM, there's a better choice.
- Hi, Phil Swift here for the
Flex Seal family of products.
Now, all the strength
of original Flex Seal
is available in portable powerful Minis.
From the toughest jobs to a simple repair,
Flex Minis are always there.
Now, with Flex minis, you can grab and go,
plus they're freaking adorable,
whether it's Flex Tape,
Flex Glue or Flex Seal.
Imagine everything you
could do with Flex Minis.
(upbeat rock music)
- I'm Alex Trebek here to tell you
about the Colonial Penn program.
If you're aged 50 to 85 and
looking to buy life insurance
on a fixed budget, remember the three Ps.
- The three Ps?
- What are the three Ps?
- The three Ps of life
insurance on a fixed budget
are price, price and price,
a price you can afford, a
price that can't increase
and a price that fits your budget.
- I'm 65 and take medications.
What's my price?
- You an get coverage for $9.95 a month.
- I just turned 80.
What's my price.
- 9.95 a month for you too.
Call now about the number one
most popular whole life insurance plan,
available through the Colonial program.
No medical exam.
No health questions.
Your acceptance is guaranteed.
So call now for free information.
- [Announcer] So 1-800-480-5533
for free information and a free gift.
That's 1-800-480-5533.
Call now.
- [Announcer] Stop the killing today.
- I don't call 'em raids.
I say they came in illegally,
and we are bringing 'em out legally.
These are people where we have the papers.
We've gone through the court system.
They'll be starting fairly soon.
But I don't call 'em raids.
- That was President Trump earlier
talking about the ICE raids
that he's been promising.
The President initially
delayed the raids on June 22nd,
the day before they were set to begin,
saying he'd give Congress two
weeks to work on asylum laws
and help the flow of migrants
at the southern US border.
But since then,
no comprehensive immigration
reform deal has been reached.
With me now is the former Acting Director
of US Immigrations and Custom
Enforcement, John Sanders.
John, good to see you again.
This is tricky.
Whether the President wants
to call them raids or not,
they are some sort of
enforcement action that require
some degree of planning,
and there were some people,
you and I talked about this last time.
There were some people
who said the President,
by continuing to announce these things
and talk about them in the
media, actually compromises
the work that he might
be trying to achieve.
- Yeah, that's absolutely right.
Listen, having been involved
in a number of these operations
and whether you call them raids
or whatever you call them,
these enforcement actions,
the number one rule
is you don't tip the target in advance
because then, when you go
to the house or the location
where you think that target
is, they're simply not there.
When we began these operations,
the beginning of the
operation, we'd get something
like 90% of the people we're going after,
but over time, they would dissipate
simply because word got
out that we were conducting
this type of operation,
and people fled and hid.
- President Trump has said that
public safety is the reason
for these raids, or he's
not now calling them raids.
But new documents actually
show that ICE is building
target lists for these
mass roundups of people
based on target numbers
that they have to meet.
So the question is do these
public documents, you know,
these things sort of hurt the argument
that there's a public
safety need for these raids?
- Ali, it's not gonna be public safety.
Listen, ICE, you know,
the problem here is this.
The President wants big numbers.
- [Ali] Yeah.
- To get big numbers, what
that requires, typically,
is you go after the most
vulnerable population.
They're the easiest to find.
They're the easiest to get.
The criminal alien population
is actually the most difficult to find.
They're adept at hiding.
They're adept at using aliases.
It takes a lot more than leg
work to get those individuals
than it does a family member with children
who are sitting in a static location.
So look, I don't think
this operation, at all,
is gonna promote public safety.
You could argue that ut
helps promote the integrity
of our immigration court
system or the board of security
but certainly not public safety.
- This other story is
the Trump administration
is threatening to impose huge fines
on people who disobey deportation orders,
some of them upwards of $300,000.
Talk to me about that.
- Well, I mean, there are
certain situations of the law
in which you can impose
a fine on an individual.
I tell you, collecting it is
a different story entirely.
You know, I'm not sure exactly
how they intend to collect it
against the majority of these individuals.
It's a bigger problem if some individual
later is able to legally
enter the United States,
but the reality, Ali, is
that the overwhelming,
the vast, vast majority of people
who are deported from this
country are never able
to legally return to the
United States, period.
- There is wide agreement on
certain immigration issues
in this country, for
instance, on the Dreamers,
the DACA kids, overwhelming
support for having them
stay here because they
have to follow rules,
they've grown up here,
they are either getting
an education or working, they
can't commit serious crimes.
But there are other disagreements
about other basic things,
and some Democratic
candidates have actually
talked about decriminalizing
the act of illegally
entering the United States.
Joe Biden has said today
that illegal border crossings
should not be decriminalized.
This is a very interesting place
that Democrats are in
because a lot of Americans
who are sympathetic to
immigrants and asylum seekers
may not believe that decriminalizing
the act of coming into the
United States illegally
should be part of the equation.
- Yeah, I agree with the
Vice President on this one.
Listen, if you come across
the border without inspecting,
that is a crime.
It's a misdemeanor offense
for your first offense,
so it's not that serious a crime,
but it should remain a crime.
Look, there is a role
for border security, border enforcement.
There's a role for immigration
enforcement in this country.
I take a lot of issue
with the manner in which
this administration is conducting that.
I think it's detrimental to public safety.
I think they're spreading
out their targets.
They're focused on vulnerable populations
instead of folks who pose
a public safety threat,
but I also worry that because
of the President's policies
that we're now looking at
immigration enforcement
writ large, and ICE and CBP in
particular, as rogue agencies
rather than questioning
the specific tactics
this administration is doing
when there is an important role
for all of our public safety
in the functions that
ICE and CBD do everyday.
- John, does what the President,
is what the President is
doing, is that playing
into the hands of the President himself
because he provokes a reaction
that causes some Democrats
to say let's decriminalize the operation,
and then the President can go out and say
that sounds like open
borders, which he's been
accusing Democrats of
embracing the whole time?
- I think that's right, Ali.
I think that, you know, look.
A lot of the President's chatter
really is idle threat, so to speak.
For example, on this raid,
he's talking about a
million people apprehended.
ICE has no capacity to arrest
anywhere near a million people.
At most, an operation like
this in a two-week period
is gonna get 5,000, and
that's probably optimistic.
But it does trigger this
kind of reaction of this
abolish ICE and this other
kind of things where people,
I think the majority of
the public recognizes
that ICE plays a critical
role in our public safety,
and I do think a lot
of people, not enough,
recognize too that ICE
is probably, you know,
is a critical player in the
counter-terrorism effort.
They save more children from exploitation
than any other federal agency.
They're the leading agency
when it comes to stopping,
you know, export control,
stopping North Korea and Iran
from getting sensitive technologies.
But you're right, it plays into the hands
when you start taking this
kind of, I hate to say it,
but extremist positions that
we need to abolish ICE entirely
or get rid of the border patrol
simply because of the
administration's policies,
not necessarily the agencies themselves.
- John, always a pleasure to talk to you.
John Sandweg, former
Acting Director of ICE.
Coming up next, we're gonna take a look
at America's energy revolution.
For the first time, the
United States is producing
more energy from renewables
than it is from coal.
I'm gonna talk to an author whose new book
profiles the man who
built one of the largest
wind energy empires in the country.
You are watching MSNBC.
- My team spent a lot of
time and money posting jobs.
We would get a flood of resumes,
but finding the right person
was nearly impossible.
My budget has to stretch,
but my time can't.
I was tired of using 12 vendors.
Then I learned that
CareerBuilder has everything,
data to help us plan, a single
source to find candidates,
marketing tools to engage them,
and the fastest background
screening on the market.
So we made the switch.
Now, we get the right person faster.
It's not just efficient.
It's smart.
- [Announcer] CareerBuilder,
work can work.
(alarm beeps)
- [Announcer] Wake up.
There's a lot that
needs to get done today,
small things, big things,
too hard to do alone things.
Day after day, you need
to get it all done.
And here to listen
and help you through it
all is Bank of America
with the expertise and knowhow you need
to reach that blissful state of doneness.
♪ Baby ♪
- [Announcer] So let's get out there.
♪ Everything is all right ♪
- [Announcer] What would
you like the power to do?
- At Hilton.com, I can choose
from all their different hotel brands,
like a DoubleTree for my cousins,
a Homewood Suites for my uncle,
a Hampton for my sister and her kids,
and the Waldorf Astoria
Beverly Hills for me.
Can I get a...
Thank you.
Book at Holton.com and get the
Hilton price match guarantee.
(stomach grumbles)
♪ When you have nausea,
heartburn, indigestion ♪
♪ Upset stomach, diarrhea ♪
- [Announcer] Try new Pepto Liquicaps
for fast relief and ultra coating.
♪ Nausea, heartburn, indigestion ♪
♪ Upset stomach ♪
- [Announcer] Get powerful relief
with new Pepto Bismol Liquicaps.
- With the money I've made on Poshmark,
I've been able to pay for
all our family's vacations.
- I could pay for my wedding
just on what I've made from Poshmark.
- I've made over $10,000,
and I was able to buy my new car.
- [Announcer] Download
the free Poshmark app now.
♪ Na na na na ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
- [Announcer] The world's first
six-function MultiPro tailgate,
available only in the next
generation GMC Sierra.
Get 20% below MSRP on next
generation 2019 GMC double cab
and and SLE crew cab models
with the standard tailgate.
(electronic music)
(plastic crunches)
(group gasps)
♪ You ♪
♪ Shine ♪
♪ Brighter than all the others ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Fly ♪
♪ Higher than the stars above you ♪
- [Announcer] Constipation
can happen all around us.
You just need to know where to look.
It can happen where people drive.
It can happen where people play.
It can happen where people exercise.
Constipation can even
happen where people work.
And it happens to all of us.
Luckily, there's Colace,
for gentle relief of
occasional constipation.
It's the number one doctor-recommended
stool softener brand.
Constipation happens.
- As you now have 76,000 points,
as part of the loyalty program,
there's a 5% discount
applied to your hotel room.
$120 for the night, please.
- Oh, 5% off as well as free Wi-Fi.
Not bad.
- $95 for the night, please, sir.
- Wait, wait.
What?
- If you use Trivago, Trivago
will compare hotel prices
from hundreds of websites
worldwide so you can often find
a better deal for your hotel
room and also free Wi-Fi.
Maybe you should try Trivago next time.
- [Announcer] Hotel?
Trivago.
- All right, we're taking a closer look
into a big economic opportunity
in the fight against climate
change, clean energy.
Here's something you may have missed.
For the first time, our capacity
for creating electricity
from renewable energy sources
surpassed that for coal.
And as the LA Times points
out, domestic coal production
and use have dropped to their
lowest levels in four decades
even though the economy is more than twice
the size it was 40 years ago.
Additionally, more coal-fired
power plants have shut down
so far during the Trump presidency
than through all eight years
of the Obama administration.
And it may have something
to do with the cost.
Let me show you a map of the
least expensive technologies
for generating electricity
across the United States by county.
Here, you can see how,
let me just show you the colors here.
The blue is wind.
Green is natural gas.
The gold is solar.
The yellow is also solar.
One of them is for utilities
that generate electricity.
The lighter yellow is for residential use.
And the gray, of course, is coal.
Take a look at that.
Coal represents the smallest proportion.
Joining me now is Russell Gold.
He's a senior energy reporter
for the Wall Street Journal
and author of a new book,
Superpower: One Man's Quest
to Transform American Energy.
It's a book that profiles
a man named Michael Skelly
who began developing wind
energy infrastructure
in the early 2000s and went on to build
the second largest wind power
company in the United States.
Russell, good to see you again.
Thank you for joining us.
- Thanks for having me.
- I wanna just read from your book.
You were talking about
Michael Skelly, and you said
he was a departure from
an earlier generation
of wind farm builders and
solar panel enthusiasts
who were more interested in
creating sustainable energy
than sustainable businesses.
Kelly wanted to make a profit
because profits would attract
new investors and money
into renewable energy.
This has long been the holy grail.
If you can make sustainable
and renewable profitable,
it can replace sort of older
fashioned, dirtier energy.
- Right, and we're seeing
that happen right now.
I mean, with the map you just brought up,
there is a big part of
the middle of the country
where you can generate
wind at a really low cost.
The question right now
is how fast can that transition happen.
How fast can you bring in
more renewables at this lower price?
- And what are the headwinds
and what are the tailwinds
for people who are trying to bring
renewable energy to market faster?
- Well, tailwinds right now,
as we've been talking about, are costs.
Renewable energy, wind,
and increasingly, solar
is the low-cost way to
generate electricity.
It beats coal.
Increasingly, it beats natural
gas, and it beats nuclear.
The headwinds are, right
now, where you can generate
renewable energy inexpensively,
is the middle of the country,
and that's not exactly
where the factories are,
the people are.
So the question is how do
you get that electricity
from the middle of the
country to the coast,
and that's one of the challenges
that Michael Skelli tackled
and I wrote about in my
new book, Superpower.
There are other headwinds
right now, and I would say
one of the major headwinds
are some of the political
and incumbents, electric
utilities and electric generators,
who don't want this change,
because quite frankly,
they're very good at
generating electricity
from coal and from some
of the older resources,
and they don't wanna make this change
because that would mean
less opportunity for them.
Most people switch on a light
and hope that it goes on.
They don't think much about the backbone
and the infrastructure of
where their power comes from.
What is required?
What are the infrastructure requirements
to make a wholesale shift
or as much of a shift as we
can make into renewables?
- Well, firs of all, yeah,
it's a great question.
And first of all, I'm not talking about
100% renewable electricity
because once you get
above about 80%, it gets really expensive.
But we can get up to 70,
80% of our electricity
coming from renewable
resources at the same prices
or perhaps even lower
than we are right now.
What's required, the big
piece of infrastructure
that's required is transmission.
These are big electricity lines
that can move gigawatts
of electricity around.
Think about it like your
interstate highways.
What we have right now are
a lot of two-lane roads
going all over the place.
And much like the 1950s, we said,
"Hey, let's build these
interstate highways
"so we can move people
quickly and efficiently
"from one city to another."
That's really what we need to do right now
with our transmission.
- Russell, I appreciate the book,
and I appreciate you coming
to talk to us about it.
Russell Gold is the
author of the new book,
Superpower: One Man's Quest
to Transform American Energy.
Still ahead, a judge gave
leniency to a teenage rape suspect
because the judge said the
teen came from a good family.
Coming up next, I'm gonna
talk about how this case
fits into broader
conversations about teens
and sexual assault with the
founder of the Me Too movement.
♪ I want it all ♪
- Burgers, donuts, Nicoise salad.
♪ And I want it now ♪
- [Announcer] Delivering from over
95,000 restaurants nationwide.
(doorbell rings)
♪ I want it all ♪
- [Announcer] If you want it all--
- [Delivery Man] Nicoise salad!
- [Announcer] You can get it all.
Grubhub, restaurants you love, delivered.
- Nick Bolton here with the
latest from Bell & Howell.
We call it Tac Visor.
Tac Visor can do things no
ordinary visor can do things
no ordinary visor can do
like block blinding glare
without blocking your view
so invisible dangers
suddenly become visible,
and enhance colors to give you vision
as sharp as an eagle's.
The secret is Bell & Howell's
light-filtering technology.
Look at that windshield.
Tell me what you see.
- A blank screen.
- Just a blank screen.
- Put down that Tac Visor
and take a look again.
- Whoa, what the--
- It's crazy.
- Best of all, Tac Visor is
easy to install in any car.
- [Announcer] Act now to get
a Tac Visor for just 19.00,
and we'll even ship it to you free.
But wait, order today
and we'll upgrade you
to our two in one Tac Visor.
Just pay a separate fee.
When the sun goes down,
use the night vision visor
to improve visibility
and block dangerous glare
from oncoming headlights.
Here's how to order.
To order, call 1-800-342-6193.
Again, that's 1-800-342-6193.
Or order online at TacVisor.com.
- This is PillPack.
Everyday, I have to remember
to take my medication.
And I hate walking around
with all of this in my purse.
Now I use PillPack.
They delivery everything right to my door
so I never miss my medication.
The best part, their service is free.
I only pay my co-pays.
Does your pharmacy do that?
Visit PillPack.com today.
- It's so easy to sell on Poshmark.
You just pick out your items,
snap a couple of photos,
and boom, it's up for sale.
When I look at my old clothes
now, I see dollar signs.
Just this month, I made a
couple of hundred dollars
on Poshmark just selling
items out of my closet.
- [Announcer] Download
the free Poshmark app now.
- We use Angie's List
because we can always
find great local pros.
- For any type of home project.
- I use Angie's List if
I need to find a plumber.
- An electrician.
- A painter.
- I always use Angie's
List because it's free.
- It's free for me to read reviews
written by real customers.
- We can check their reputation
and make sure they do quality work.
- And now, to save time,
Angie's List can actually
match my project to a few
qualified pros who can do the job.
- [Announcer] To get the most
reviews from real customers
all for free, go to angieslist.com today.
- [Announcer] This is not just any cruise.
This MSC Cruises, one of
the largest cruise lines
in the world, where every
detail is beyond just ordinary.
You won't walk on just any stairs.
These steps are covered
in Swarovski crystals.
There's not just one performance to see.
There's a different show every night.
On an MSC Cruise, you won't
be served just any meal.
You'll enjoy freshly prepared
international cuisine.
And you won't explore just any destination
or experience just any ship.
You'll cruise the Caribbean
on the best new cruise ship,
the revolutionary MSC Seaside.
Book a seven-night Caribbean cruise
and get unlimited drinks and
Wi-Fi from only 549 per person.
That's right.
Get unlimited drinks,
including wine, beer,
missed drinks and more.
Call MSC Cruises at 800-615-0726.
Visit msccruises.com or
your travel agent today.
- He came from a good family.
A judge used that excuse to show leniency
to a suspect accused of sexual
assault and is prompting
renewed debate about rape
culture in the United States.
The case comes from New
Jersey, where that judge
denied a request to try a
16-year-old teen as an adult.
The suspect is accused of
raping an intoxicated girl,
recording the assault and
sending the video to friends
with the text "when your first
time having sex was rape."
In New York and New Jersey,
prosecutors can request
to send a juvenile case to
adult court for serious crimes
if the accused is 15 years old or older,
but the family court judge
denied prosecutor's motion,
saying the assault
wasn't rape and writing,
"This young man comes from a good family
"who put him into an excellent school
"where he was doing extremely well."
He also added, "He is clearly a candidate
"for not just college but
probably for a good college.
"His scores for college
entry were very high."
The state appeals court
has already overturned
the judge's decision,
but the case underscores
a fundamental issue
in the way this country views
rape and sexual assault.
To talk about those issues,
I turn to Tarana Burke.
She is the founder of the Me Too movement.
And you have, during the
time, this has become
such a big and public movement,
really approached this
with a degree of sophistication
that says we are working
from a low base of understanding
about these things.
And what is the best way
to get us to understand
what sexual violence is all about?
- Well, this is why the
conversation has to shift
about what Me Too is because
the thing that's glaring to me
in this whole case is that
there's no conversation
about the survivor,
about her grades, how
her life was changed,
what happened to her, how it affected her,
and it's focused totally
on this perpetrator.
And that's what happens
a lot because people,
what I've realized more
so in the last two years
is people don't understand
the lifecycle of a survivor.
They don't understand
what sexual violence is
or what it does to the
people who experience it.
And so you have cases like this happen
where you have larger
narratives that are patriarchal
and misogynistic and veer
towards what men and boys need
and what their lives and
livelihoods, how that's affected
more so than the people
who they victimized.
- There was the same conversation
on college campuses--
- Absolutely.
- Where we talked about
whether boys were being,
having their futures ruined
because of the way their
assaults were being treated.
What does success look like
for you on these fronts?
Because I don't think your view
is that everybody who's a perpetrator
needs to have all of the
books thrown at them--
- No.
- But we're not listening
to the other side.
We're not balancing out victim's rights
with perpetrator's rights.
- This is the thing.
When Me Too went viral,
you had millions of people
literally come together and say,
"My life has been affected by this thing."
We've yet to talk about that thing.
We've yet to unpack
what sexual violence is
and what it really looks
like in this country.
It's not about these high profile cases
as much as it is about
these kinds of cases.
And so what it's gonna take
is a shift in the narrative
about how we talk about sexual violence
and then also how we
talk about this movement.
This is a movement that's
about healing and action.
And the healing and
action part, a lot of that
is based on how we educate
people around sexual violence,
how we educate people around
what survival looks like.
When we shift the narrative, we have,
when people are more educated about this,
these are people who vote,
people who make the legislative decisions,
they have to understand this differently.
It can't come from this
sort of pop culture,
salacious headline place.
It has to come to a place
where you really have
empathy and understanding
for what survival looks like.
- How do we get there?
Because you and I have
talked about this before.
When the people accused of
sexual harassment or assault
are not media or not politicians
or not CEOs of major companies,
has this trickled down
to help victims of sexual
violence who don't have a name,
who are homeless, who are immigrants,
who are single mothers,
who work on a factory floor?
- That's our work.
That's our work.
That's what the Me Too movement is about.
We have an organization,
and we are part of a
large spectrum of people
who are doing this work on the ground.
I'm appreciative of coming
into spaces like this
and being able to talk
about it on a national front
because this is how we change it.
People need to understand
that this work is happening.
It was happening before Me Too went viral
and it's continuing to happen.
Part of what we do is educate
people about what this is.
Part of the work that
other organizations do,
other national organizations,
National Women's Law Center
and other organizations like
that are educating people
but we're also galvanizing people.
People keep asking, "What
is the Me Too movement
"gonna do about X," and I'm trying to say
we're all the Me Too movement.
You don't put it on one person.
- [Ali] It's all of our behavior.
- It's all of us.
We all have to be responsive.
We all have to be responsible.
When something like this happens,
we all have to be outraged and push back.
Historically, judicial
systems and political systems
have to catch up to where the people are.
The people realize that
stuff like this is awful,
but we have to push back
and raise our voices
so that the court systems know
and so that the politicians
know that we won't stand for it.
- [Ali] Tarana, we appreciate
you coming and helping us
get smarter about this
and helping our audience.
Tarana Burke is the founder
of the Me Too movement.
- Thank you.
- That wraps up this hour for me.
I'm back Monday, one p.m.
Eastern, for Velshi & Ruhle.
Have yourselves a great weekend,
and thank you for watching.
- My experience with
USAA has been excellent.
They really appreciate military
family, and it really shows.
- With all that USAA offers,
why go with anybody else?
And we know their rates are good.
We know that they're always
gonna take care of us.
- It was instant savings,
and I should have changed a long time ago.
- It was funny because when we would call
another insurance company, they would say,
"Oh, we can't beat USAA."
- We're the Webber family.
- We're the Tennys.
- We're the Hales, and
we're USAA members for life.
- [Announcer] Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
- [Announcer] Parents have a
way of imagining the worst,
especially when your easily
distracted teenager has the car.
At Subaru, we're taking
on distracted driving
with sensors that alert you
when your eyes are off the road.
The all new Subaru Forester,
the safest Forester ever.
- Going to the Shawn
Mendes Verizon Up concert
was like an out-of-body experience.
- [Announcer] Why the Yousafzai
sisters chose Verizon.
- We were right in front of him.
- Dead center, front row.
Actually, Zamila, you
touched Shawn Mendes.
- She touched Shawn Mendes.
- Yeah, I touched him.
He like held my hand for a while,
and then we got to meet
him after, which was like--
- Another surprise.
- Yeah.
We love Verizon even more now.
I'll never forget that day ever.
- [Announcer] The network
more people rely on
gives you more, like thousands of tickets
to concerts, festivals and private shows,
and big savings on our best phones.
- Oh, my gosh.
Wow!
Who am I?
- Wow, is that really me? (laughs)
- [Jonathan] Hi, I'm Jonathan Greenhut,
the CEO of Plexaderm.
We've created the best offer yet
with our Plexaderm 10-minute challenge.
All it takes is 10 minutes
to reduce the appearance
of under eye bags,
wrinkles and crow's feet.
Plexaderm works so well, makeup artists
and even people across the country
look and feel years younger in minutes.
- Hi, guys.
My name is Sandy Maranesi.
I'm a professional hair and makeup artist.
And one of the number one
question that I always get
in my chair is, "Can you
make me look younger?"
Now I can really say to people,
"Yes, I can make you look younger."
- My name is Robin, and this
is what Plexaderm does for me.
- [Jonathan] The instant results
are from naturally based
silicates found in shell rock.
Once applied, your skin
tightens and firms.
Take action with the
Plexaderm 10-minute challenge.
Get up to 50% off the normal retail price,
plus get free...