- As far as the squad
itself, after the game,
they posted a video of
most of the team dancing
to the 2007 banger "Rock Yo Hips".
If you don't know it, that sucks for you.
But the fact that this song
is what brings this team
together is amazing.
Oh, and the name of the group who made it,
probably describes both
country's histories
of money making quite well, Crime Mob.
God bless them, and God bless America.
NFL Live's next.
We're back on July 11th.
I'm Clinton Yates, kiddos.
Got it!
(dramatic music)
- NFL Live packed with
special guest stars today.
Jaguar's quarterback Jalen
Ramsey joins the show live
to talk about how the Jags
bounced back this year.
We'll also talk to Browns
tight end David Njoku
about all the excitement in Cleveland
and what's ahead for the Browns.
And since tomorrow is Independence Day,
we will show you some of
the best independent plays
in NFL history.
You'll wanna stick around,
if only to find out
what we mean by that.
Oh yes, if you just can't
get your holiday weekend
started without hearing
90 more minutes of NFL
off-season content, you have
come to the right place.
Dan Graziano here with Damien
Woody and Mike Tannenbaum.
Lots to get to on the eve
of your long holiday
weekend, but we will start
with the situation
regarding Ezekiel Elliott.
The Cowboys superstar
running back met Tuesday
with NFL commissioner Roger Goodell
to discuss a recent
incident involving Elliott
and a security guard in Las Vegas.
Elliott was briefly detained
but not arrested in the incident.
Given his history with the
league's personal conduct
policy, the commissioner
called him in for a discussion.
Following that discussion,
Elliott posted the following
statement on Twitter.
"Earlier today I met with the commissioner
"to share with him what
occurred in Las Vegas
"and what I have learned
from that incident.
"I've worked hard to make better decisions
"and to live up to the high standards
"that are expected of me.
"I have failed to do that here,
and I made a poor decision.
"I apologized to Kyle Johnson,"
that's the security guard in question,
"at the time and I meant it.
"I need to work harder to
ensure I do not put myself
"in compromised situations in the future.
"I am rededicating myself
to use all of the resources
"that the league has made available.
"But in the end, it is up to
me and I am determined not
"to be in this position again."
Why is this a big deal?
Well, partially because of the warning
commissioner Roger
Goodell issued to Elliott
when he suspended him in 2017.
In his suspension letter at that time
Goodell wrote to Elliott,
"You must have no further
adverse involvement
"with law enforcement, and must not commit
"any additional violations
of league policies.
"You should understand
that another violation
"of this nature may
result in your suspension
"or potential banishment from the NFL."
So look, we are not here to make equations
or comparisons between
things that Ezekiel Elliott
did in the past and
what this incident was,
but here he is sort of making
the wrong kinds of headlines again.
And being called into the
commissioner's office,
no small thing for a
player in his situation.
So Mike, if you're in the front office
of this team, and you have
a player in this situation.
He's got a contract situation coming up
over the next couple years.
What kind of conversation do you need
to have with him at this time?
- Yeah you need to have a direct, honest,
and very difficult conversation.
You have to let him
know that this behavior
is unacceptable and this
is more than one instance.
And as you said, Dan, maybe
it's not as significant
as the one that happened in the past.
But from the Cowboys organization
what I would tell him is,
"Look, we're gonna hit pause
on your contract negotiations."
There's four other players
right now that the Cowboys have.
Dak Prescott their starting quarterback,
Amari Cooper, who they traded
for from the Oakland Raiders.
And two good defensive
players in Jalen Smith
and Byron Jones.
All four of those players
are going into the last year
of their respective contracts.
They have played well and
acted flawlessly off the field.
I would have that conversation
with Ezekiel Elliott to say,
"While we appreciate what
you've done on the field,
"right now you're under
contract for this year.
"We have the option for 2020,
"and we can franchise you the year after.
"So basically, for the next three years,
"we can control your rights.
"And because of the way you've acted,
"we're hitting pause and it may
not be what you wanna hear."
But that's the conversation
you need to have with the player.
- Damien, from the
standpoint of a teammate
of a guy like this in this situation,
what conversation are you having with him?
- Well listen, I think it's just important
that you're available.
Because for a veteran,
at the end of the day,
if the guy who basically stirs
the drink isn't available,
you're affecting my money.
You're affecting everybody
in the organization.
I mean, think about it.
Jason Garrett is, this is
like his contract year.
This is his year, do or die year,
and you're putting yourself,
you're Ezekiel Elliott,
you're putting yourself in
a compromising situation
where you could be potentially suspended
and not available to the team.
There's so much riding on
the Dallas Cowboys this year
that it's all hands on deck.
And if I'm a veteran in
the locker room I'm like,
"Dude, okay, let's chill out, calm down.
"You can't keep putting
yourself out there,
"because you're hurting
everybody, not just yourself."
- And Damien, to your point
about how Ezekiel Elliott
stirs the drink, look at Dak Prescott,
he has some passer rating of
122 from when it's play action.
And the reason that's so effective is,
the opposing defense is
worrying about Ezekiel Elliott.
So, that is not by coincidence
that he has such a high passer rating
from when they're in play action,
because everything's gonna
be keyed on Ezekiel Elliott.
So, if he's not available,
it does disrupt.
Now look, Amari Cooper was
a very valuable acquisition,
but without Ezekiel Elliott,
that offense is a lot easier to defend.
- So, no question obviously
about the importance
of Ezekiel Elliott to
the Cowboys' offense.
They struggled without him in
2017 when he was suspended.
We await word from the
commissioner's office
on whether he will face discipline
for this latest incident
and if that word comes in
the next hour and a half,
we will of course bring it to you.
In the meantime though,
we're gonna move on
to the sillier portion of our show.
(laughing)
("The Stars and Stripes Forever")
Tomorrow is the 243rd anniversary
of the signing of the
Declaration of Independence.
We didn't have access to Thomas Jefferson,
we have Damien Woody and
we have Mike Tannenbaum,
but even though they might
not have been the first choice
on declarations, Jefferson
couldn't make it.
We've decided to ask them of
some declarations of their own.
So, basically what this is
going to be is something
you feel strongly about,
something you feel like declaring
about the upcoming NFL season.
It doesn't have to be about life, liberty,
or the pursuit of happiness.
It has to be about football.
Damien, start with you.
What's your first declaration of the day?
- So, my declaration is that Kirk Cousins
will be the best quarterback
in the NFC North this year.
- Whoa, whoa.
- Yes.
I'm going out there on Kirk Cousins
and the Minnesota Vikings.
I love what the Vikings did in the draft,
adding a couple pieces up
front on the offensive line.
They have arguably the
best wide receiver tandem
in Thielen, and in Diggs on the outside.
They drafted Irv Smith, you know,
tight end from Alabama to
go along with Kyle Rudolph.
And obviously Dalvin
Cook in the backfield.
So everything right now is ready-made.
Mike T. is trying to jump in on this,
but I'm not gonna let him jump in.
I am adamant right now that Kirk Cousins
is gonna get it done in
the NFC North this year.
Don't make me look like
a fool, Kirk Cousins.
- Yeah, we're gonna have an
NFL constitutional crisis
because, let me tell ya.
(laughing)
I got the words Aaron Rodgers.
- Listen, I understand Aaron
Rodgers is in the NFC North
and I got much love and
respect for Aaron Rodgers,
but I also look at this.
What did the Green Bay
Packers, how much addition
did the Green Bay Packers
add to Aaron Rodgers,
you know that offense,
to help Aaron Rodgers
this upcoming year?
Not much.
I didn't see much of anything this year.
- Guys to develop.
- Like I said,
with Kirk Cousins this is the year.
He's getting paid a boatload of money.
The Minnesota Vikings
drafted guys up front
to help on their offensive line,
and I think this is the
year that Kirk Cousins
makes a statement in the
National Football League.
- So if he does, what does
that mean for the Vikings?
How far can they take it?
- They can go to the Super Bowl.
- Oh, boy.
Vikings.
- If you have--
- This is how we do declarations.
- If you haven't figured it out by now,
I'm pretty bullish on
the Minnesota Vikings.
- But Damien, we know
the sign of great players
when they make everybody
else around them better.
Isn't that one of Aaron
Rodgers's greatest strengths,
is that he could elevate
the play of his teammates?
And I agree, Minnesota's
had a good offseason,
Dalvin Cook's coming back.
But at the end of the
day, isn't Aaron Rodgers
the better player than Kirk Cousins?
- Yeah, Cousins had the
highest completion percentage
of any NFC North quarterback last year
and the most touchdown passes.
But as he would tell you,
he was only 1-6-1 against
teams with winning records.
Obviously you gotta do better than that.
Mike, what do you got to compete with that
Damien Woody declaration?
- Well, I will stay
with the same position.
(laughing)
And I'm going to declare that Kyler Murray
will not play in 16 games
And my concern for Kyler Murray
is his play style is
very similar to someone
like Marcus Mariota.
Marcus Mariota, throughout
his career has never
played in 16 games.
And while Kyler Murray
is a dynamic athlete,
because of his build,
I think at some point
it's gonna be hard for
him to answer the bell
at some Sunday this season.
And I could see him
missing at least one game.
So my declaration is, Kyler Murray,
based on his size, based
on the way he plays,
he will not play in 16 games.
- Very interesting,
because a lot of excitement
about Kyler Murray and that
Kliff Kingsbury offense
there in Arizona the first year.
But he is a scrambler.
He scrambled 41 times last year,
ninth most of any FBS quarterback.
That's certainly going
to be part of his game.
They say that that helps
when they are questions
on the offensive line.
Do you buy it, or do they
need to be better up front?
- No, they need to be better up front.
I'm a big believer, listen.
Football isn't very
complicated, you gotta block,
you gotta tackle, catch and
all those type of things.
And what we saw from the
Arizona Cardinals last year,
they couldn't block their
way out of a wet paper bag.
So, this is gonna be a
situation that bears watching
as far as Kyler Murray and
protecting him moving forward.
- [Mike] By the way,
we heard the same spiel
a couple years ago when
I was the general manager
of the Jets, we were trying to sign
Damien Woody the offensive lineman,
he reminded us then about how important
the offensive line is.
- [Damien] Yeah, and
listen, the tape don't lie.
The tape doesn't lie.
- It was a softball, I
knew I was setting him up.
I like to take care of
Damien on the summer show.
- That's right, that's right.
- To get through together.
We got more to do, though.
Coming up on NFL Live,
as we mentioned earlier,
Independence Day is tomorrow.
We're not on the air tomorrow,
we're gonna celebrate it a day early
with the NFL's most independent plays.
Looking at the guys who can
do it all by themselves.
Speaking of doing it all,
Cam Newton may be rehabbing
his throwing arm but that
doesn't mean he can't catch.
Which quarterback has the best hands?
Damien Woody's gonna take
a shot at ranking those.
Plus, Jalen Ramsey, one
of the top trash-talkers
in the game, but has he changed his ways?
We'll bring him in live
and he will tell us.
- I go out there with a little swag.
Sometimes, I just go out there, and just,
I just let the receiver know every play.
Hey, this gonna be a long game for you.
You're trash compared to me.
(exciting music)
- I got a very, very
small loan from my father.
- You gotta start somewhere.
- I'm a reporter from the New York Times.
Bank statements, tax returns.
Thousands of copied
records, deeds, mortgages.
1995 showed that he was bleeding money.
Go through it all, understand it all.
- Holy.
- Number by number.
Brick by brick.
- That's when we realized that's fraud.
- [Trump] I built this
empire, I did it by myself.
- [Narrator] New, for summer,
it's Bud Light Lemon Tea,
brewed with real lemon peels
and aged on real tea leaves.
Yes, it's real.
No, you're not dreaming.
Hey, don't do that.
(funky music)
- Doesn't that cloud right
there look like a penguin?
- That looks just like your house
that's being burglarized, they're stealing
your TV right there.
Oh, and right there, it's
a bear destroying your car.
- You need a vacation.
- You know, Chris, some of
us don't have an offseason.
- [Narrator] Pieces or cups?
Pieces or cups?
Pieces in cups!
Man, we're killing it over here, huh?
Not sorry, Reese's
(upbeat music)
♪ Summer nights, keeping me up ♪
♪ I wanna waste time just looking up ♪
♪ Sky full of stars mind wandering far ♪
♪ Like we're 16 dreaming in the dark ♪
♪ Love the wind in my
hair as I drive my car ♪
♪ It makes me feel free ♪
- [Narrator] Now, get exceptional offers
at the Infiniti Plus Summer Sales Event
- [Narrator] In every
trip, there's room for more
than just the business you came for.
Whether that's taking in every moment,
or capturing a moment worth bringing back.
That's room for possibility.
- Yay.
(exhaling)
(bottle opening)
(bouncing)
(exhaling)
(train dinging)
(bottle opening)
(splashing)
(exhaling)
- I switched to Miralax
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives forcefully
stimulate the nerves
in your colon.
MiraLAX works with the water in your body
to unblock your system naturally.
And it doesn't cause
bloating, cramping, gas,
or a sudden urgency.
MiraLAX, look for the pink cap.
- So I can buy from Enterprise Car Sales,
and you'll take any trade-in?
- That's right.
- Great.
There you go.
- Well, it does need to be a vehicle.
- But, I need this out of my house.
With a fair, transparent
value for every trade-in.
Enterprise makes it easy.
(reporters chattering)
- Yes?
- We were all shocked that
the Odellicatessans first pick
of the fantasy draft would be a rookie.
Who shaped your strategy?
- At this time--
- I'll take this one, Lindsey.
It was mine.
- Rollin' With My Homies?
- I'm sorry, my lawyer says I
can't speak at this moment so.
- Honey Bunches of Oats,
is there any connection
between your attire and
your record last season?
- Oh, no.
- [Narrator] Do you
take your fantasy draft
as serious as we do?
Prove it, for the chance to
have Commissioner Goodell
host your league's draft
live at NFL headquarters.
- [Narrator] NFL Live
is brought to you by,
Pizza Hut, no one out-pizzas the Hut.
- It's something that my
mom always warns me about,
you only get one set of teeth.
- From ear to ear, he's always smiling.
(laughing)
- I'm happy to be a part of that.
- He's always kidding
around and keeping it light.
- If I'm feeling good, I
know that it's gonna be
contagious enough around others.
- [Dan] Why is Cam Newton
smiling, because he's awesome.
He can run, he can throw,
and apparently he can catch.
Recently, in an Under Armour
camp showing off his hands
running a go route, catching
a one-hander behind his back.
Odell Beckham has got nothing on Cam.
So, got us to thinking as
we do in the offseason,
and I know Damien always says
we don't give quarterbacks
enough attention around here.
One of the most best
quarterback catches of all-time.
This Mohammed Sanu pass had
trouble written all over it
until Andy Dalton made a leaping catch
to bail out his receiver.
Took it rest of the way to the endzone,
finishing with a sweet dive to the pylon.
Look at Andy laying out.
- [Damien] He could've
gotten smoked right there.
- [Dan] What about Andrew Luck in college.
He had a couple of targets last season,
maybe it's because Frank Reich took a look
at this one-handed catch he
made when he was at Stanford.
The catch is impressive enough,
but he also gets that foot in-bounds.
- [Damien] Wow.
- [Dan] Not a catch in
the NFL though, right?
- [Damien] Not a catch in the NFL.
- [Dan] Gotta work on that toe tap.
- [Damien] Gotta drag it.
- Great athlete though.
- Yeah, no kidding.
- That's pretty clear there.
But I don't think they're
gonna have him doing
too much of that.
Of course, the Philly special.
How do we forget the Philly special?
First catch by a quarterback
in Super Bowl history.
Nick Foles's acting job before the snap
might've been even more
impressive than the catch itself.
But what a moment, all-time moment in NFL,
and certainly Eagles history.
So obviously, quarterbacks
are all-around athletes too.
(Damien sighs)
In some cases.
- Yeah.
- I know, I know, it hurts you.
- It hurts.
- To give this much praise to
quarterbacks, but here we are.
It's July 3rd, man, we're gonna do it.
We're gonna grind out this content.
Damien, I want your list of
the most versatile quarterbacks
currently playing in the NFL.
The guys who can do remarkable things.
- Yeah, so number five, we're gonna start
with this big guy right
here in Josh Allen.
The thing I love about, Josh,
everyone talks about the
huge cannon arm, right?
He can throw it all over the place.
But look it here, I didn't know he was
an Olympic hurdler as well.
I mean, just jumping
over the Minnesota Viking
defender right there.
I mean, that was a huge play
in that Buffalo Bills win
up in Minnesota last year.
So, this dude is a tremendous athlete.
Look for him to have a big year this year.
- He led the Bills rushing last year.
- That's right, that's right.
- You guys were looking at
quarterbacks a little bit,
you know, with the Dolphins two years ago.
What'd you think him coming out?
- Yeah, everything that Damien said.
He's big, strong, can make all the throws.
He's gonna have to learn how
to kind of corral that in,
so he can play a full season.
He's gonna be taking a lot of hits.
- You mean play quarterback?
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- Number four, what you got?
- Number four right here,
we're gonna go right here
with Mitchell Trubisky.
I mean, listen, I almost
wanna call Mitchell,
Mitchell Vick.
You look at this run right
here, he started at the 15,
goes all the way back to the 30.
This play here against
the New England Patriots.
Just watch this guy run.
He's a really good athlete.
He can really run with
the football in his hand.
Dangerous both throwing
and running the football.
So again, guy just
takes off in the pocket.
He's pulling away from people here.
Listen, when a defense gotta
defend both of those aspects
of a quarterback, makes it awfully tough.
- I think he's done a
great job of designing
an offense to play to his strength.
Brought a lot of those Andy
Reid concepts from Kansas City.
That's a hard offense to defend.
- Number three?
- So, number three, get you a quarterback
that can do both.
We got Big Ben here.
Listen, we all know Big Ben
is a future Hall of Famer,
but how about this?
How about with the pooch punt right here.
Playing situational
football, at that Mike T.
Situational football,
downed the ball inside
the one yard line, huge play.
Again, Big Ben showing off his prowess
with another pooch punt.
Setting it up right here, setting it up
for the special teams, so.
When you got a quarterback
that can not only
go out there and throw for 300 yards,
but can set your field position up,
guy deserves to get paid.
- You know, he must enjoy that.
They call that pooch punt,
he must be loving it.
- Oh, absolutely, absolutely.
- Must be hard to keep a
poker face. Number two?
- So, number two, we got Killa
Cam, Cam Newton right here.
- Number two, huh?
- Listen, Cam Newton is
obviously a physical freak
of nature, you're going
to see why right here.
That little trick play, boom!
Dropped the hammer down
on the defensive lineman.
How many quarterbacks are willing
to throw their shoulder in
on a defensive lineman right here.
Just knocking him down to the ground.
Cam's not a small, Cam's
a big boy at quarterback.
So, it really doesn't surprise me that he
knocked that defensive
lineman on his butt,
but again, an offensive
lineman can appreciate
a quarterback that's
willing to throw his body
in there for the play.
- He is physically imposing.
When you see him come out for warm-ups.
You think wow, this guy could be a lot.
He is a physically imposing player
that happens to be a quarterback.
- That's right, that's right.
- Couldn't even do a quarterback segment
without you talking about
blocking, unbelievable.
- And then obviously.
- This guy.
- This right here, Hall
of Famer right here,
Patrick Mahomes.
And listen, we always
talk about, as a father,
you always talk about having your kids
involved in more than one sport.
Well here's why, you see
a guy in Patrick Mahomes.
Great football player,
also great baseball player.
You see him throwing from
all different arm angles.
Being able to make plays,
throwing with his left hand.
I mean, he did this time
after after time again
during the season, and
that's what made him special.
No-look passes, and to
me that's the product
of playing multiple sports.
They kind of intertwine with each other.
And the big reason why he
was the NFL MVP last year.
- Mike, when you're
evaluating quarterbacks,
and you look at all-around play.
How much does it factor
in, how athletic they are,
or whether they can do
other stuff like this?
- It's really important.
Look, it starts with accuracy.
But being able to buy a second chance.
You know, we touched on
it earlier in the show
about Kyler Murray playing behind that
Arizona offensive line.
The fact that he'll be able to avoid,
move up in the pocket,
sometimes it's not about
just gaining yards, but it's
about avoiding the big hit,
extending the play, keeping
your eyes down the field.
It's really important, and that's a skill
that transfers from college to pros.
And, as you mentioned, Damien,
what Patrick Mahomes did at
Texas Tech in that offense
we're seeing with the Kansas City Chiefs.
- Do you guys know, trivia time here.
Do you guys know which
active NFL quarterback
has the most career catches?
(sighs)
They don't know.
- No.
- Drew Brees, he has eight.
- Wow.
- How about that?
- Eight?
- Really?
- Yeah, we'll run them
back, we'll run them back.
Maybe another show, later in the summer,
we'll do Drew Brees highlight catches.
And maybe have you rank them.
- For the content, we need the content.
When we come back, Jalen
Ramsey's not been shy
about sharing his opinion on things
like quarterback rankings.
Now, he's got a Super Bowl
MVP leading his offense.
Does Jalen think Nick
Foles can lead this team
to a championship?
He will join us live.
- Remember that degree
you got in taxation?
Of course you don't, because you didn't.
Your job isn't understanding tax code,
it's understanding why that
will get him a body like that.
Move!
That.
Your job isn't doing hard work, here.
It's making her do hard work
and getting paid for it.
- [Narrator] Snap and sort your expenses
to save over 4,600 at tax time.
- Jody, it's time to get yours.
- [Narrator] QuickBooks, backing you.
- [Narrator] The hamsters,
run hopelessly in their cage,
content on their endless quest to nowhere.
But perhaps this year, a more
exhilarating endeavor awaits.
Defy the laws of human nature
at the Summer of Audi Sales Event.
Get exceptional offers now.
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] Discover a
new wave of refreshment,
crafted using our unique,
brew pure process.
White Claw Hard Seltzer,
nothing tastes quite like it.
(mellow rock music)
- [Narrator] Home, it's
so much more than a house.
It's your own freshly cut fairway.
For over 30 years, Rocket
Mortgage has helped
millions of Americans finance
the home of their dreams.
- Nope, nope.
- [Narrator] So you can focus
on making your house, home.
Rocket Mortgage, push
button, get mortgage.
- [Mom] Look, make a wish.
- I wish for a Biggie Bag from Wendy's.
- I wish everyone loves
each other, and was all--
- That is a great wish, Jimmy.
- [Narrator] Get a Bacon Double Stack
with a quarter-pound
of fresh beef, nuggets,
fries, and a drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
- [Narrator] Break down every
dinger with launch angle,
exit velocity, apex, and distance.
The T-Mobile Home Run
Derby Stat Cast Edition,
powered by AWS.
Monday at eight on ESPN2.
- I'm Tracy Morgan, and
I'm hosting the 2019 ESPYS.
I first met Brady in 2002,
and neither of our bodies
have changed a bit.
Hey, hey, eyes up here my man.
This is prosperity.
- [Narrator] Personal training
just got a lot more personal.
- Good morning, from Bora Bora.
- [Narrator] Introducing
the all-new X-Series
from NordicTrack.
- Ready to get started on
today's workout, let's go.
- [Narrator] All you have
to do is press start.
- So glad you can join me
this morning, let's go.
- [Narrator] Your trainer
controls the speed.
- We'll take it up to 60 percent.
- [Narrator] Incline, decline,
and duration of your workout.
This is what results in your
home on your terms looks like.
You can take advantage of our
special 36 month financing
for qualified buyers.
Only at NordicTrack.com.
- [MLK] We hold these
truths to be self-evident
that all men are created equal.
- [JFK] The torch has been passed
to a new generation of Americans.
- [Barbara Jordan] The American Dream
need not forever be deferred.
- As the richest, and the
most powerful country.
(gentle music)
- [Jalen] Hey, if you dream
about catching this ball on me,
you better wake up and apologize.
I go out there with a little swag.
You soft today, like, you weak today.
- [Announcer] It's picked
off by Jalen Ramsey.
It looked like Ramsey came over the top.
- [Mike] He's a physical corner
who can suffocate any receiver.
- [Jalen] Sometimes, I just go out there.
I'll let the receiver know every play,
hey this is gonna be a long game for you.
I'll call out their route
just to let them know,
look, I'm on my game today.
- [Announcer] Intercepted by Jalen Ramsey.
- [Jalen] You're trash compared to me.
(catchy rock music)
- Very pleased to welcome in to NFL Live,
Jaguars cornerback, Jalen
Ramsey, who joins us today
from London, England.
Jalen, I gotta start here, I was dismayed
when you recently told our Adam Scheffter
that you were going to
get out of the business
of evaluating quarterbacks.
You were so good at it, why
have you decided to stop?
- Really, I went through most
of them last year, I think.
To be honest, I didn't think
I needed to do it again.
My opinions were my opinions,
and they didn't really change too much.
So yeah, I just didn't feel
the need to do it again.
I wanted to pump up Nick
a little bit at mini-camp,
and I was excited to see Nick out there.
So I wanted to pump Nick up a little bit.
But yeah, just got away
from it for a little bit.
- I'm gonna ask you about
Nick in a little bit,
but I'm wondering as you went
around the league last year,
did you hear a lot about
that interview that you gave
where you talked about
all the quarterbacks?
People give you a hard time,
or tell you you were right?
- Yeah, I mean, it was opinion-based.
Exactly how it went, we were
just talking a little bit,
and we started off naming,
like, who I thought
were the top five quarterbacks.
And then we started going
down the whole list,
and I was kind of saying,
kind of still keeping
that mindframe, like
yeah he's not top five,
or he's overrated, his this,
that, he's sorry, he's good.
Whatever, he gets the job done.
Whatever I was saying about
each every quarterback.
Yeah, just giving some opinions.
Some people, of course,
they're gonna agree,
and some people are not gonna agree.
Everybody's entitled to their own opinion.
- Absolutely, we enjoy it.
But you mentioned, your new
quarterback, Nick Foles,
joining the Jaguars as
a free agent this year.
What's the one thing about him
that jumps out at your so far
that you may not have known
before he was your teammate?
- I mean, just how well
he practices, I guess.
Because, I've of course
never practiced with him.
And those three days in
mini-camp, I got to see
how he comes out there and he works hard.
And he pushes the guys
and he leads the offense.
It was truly impressive.
I had already known and heard about
how good of a teammate
he was, and how good
of a person he was in general.
Just seeing him in the locker
room, being in his presence,
and, you know, communicating with him
in our few interactions,
it was super nice.
- So, starting quarterback
is obviously a major change
on any NFL team.
What's the biggest
difference in the Jaguars
this year versus last year
having made that change?
- Yeah, I do feel like it's an upgrade.
Of course, I was a fan of Blake.
Blake was a really good
teammate to everybody.
But, you know, having Nick,
a former Super Bowl champion,
and Super Bowl MVP, we have
supreme confidence in him.
And we think that he's
going to do a good job
of leading our offense.
Of course, on the
defensive side of the ball,
we are overflowing with
confidence over there,
and talent, and guys who we think
can get the job done
over there on that side.
So now, we've got somebody outside.
To roll with Leonard, and DD,
and all the other guys over there.
So we're super excited.
- So yeah, the defense
obviously completely dominant.
Two seasons ago, you guys
came agonizingly close
to the Super Bowl.
And then last year,
obviously, a disappointment
for the team all the way around.
So what gives you the confidence
that this can be closer to 2017 than 2018?
- We're just gonna embrace
the journey, to be honest.
People say, like, trust the
process and stuff like that.
I really don't even believe in that,
because we can make how
ever many plans we want to
in our head, and whatever
we feel like the process is.
But it's truly gonna be a journey.
It's gonna be ups and
down, and highs and lows,
and we have to roll with all of them.
We have to roll with the highs,
we have to roll with the lows,
and we have to push
through it to make sure
that we are in position
to win the division,
win the conference and
go to the Super Bowl
and compete for Super Bowls.
- You've quickly
established yourself as one
of the better players in
your position in the league.
But the NFL being what it is, you're still
a ways away from free agency.
The Jaguars picked up your
contract option for 2020.
- Yeah.
- Any extension talks yet,
or is that still on the backburner?
- It's on the back burner right now,
but that's completely
fine with how first-round
contracts are structured
right now in this current CBA,
teams have a lot of leverage.
They can pick up the fifth year option,
so unlike other guys, who outplay their
rookie contract and can re-up right now
and get basically what they're worth.
First rounders don't have that luxury.
We have the fifth year
option, then after that,
they can either franchise
tag, and you know,
do any and every which
thing that they want to do.
They have a little bit of leverage,
but I'm gonna let my agent
handle a lot of that.
I'm gonna just focus
on what I can focus on,
and play ball and help the team win
while I'm here in Jacksonville.
Hopefully, I'm here for a long time,
and when it's time to open
up contract negotiations,
we'll see how things go.
Of course, we wanted to
get it done this year,
but it won't get done this year.
And hey, it is what it is.
I'm moving forward from that.
We've talked with the
Jaguars and everybody
who's in charge of that,
so they know what's up.
They know how it's gonna roll.
- So you're coming to
us from London today.
And obviously, the big story
over here in the States
is the US women's soccer
team beating England
in the World Cup yesterday.
And what's caught the
attention of a lot of people
is Alex Morgan, right, the
tea sipping celebration
of the goal.
This has become a big,
huge thing over here
and probably there as well.
What are your thoughts on
it as a known trash-talker?
- I loved it, of course.
Just like you said, I've been
known to trash-talk, myself,
and do a little bit of it here and there.
So I loved it.
I thought it was very fitting, of course,
because of who they played, obviously.
And sealing it up, why not have some fun?
I mean, we're professional
athletes of course,
but we're also entertainers in a sense.
We want to keep everything interesting.
So now, she gave people
everything to talk about,
a lot to talk about.
I think it's cool, I think it's good.
- Jalen Ramsey, thank you
so much for joining us
on NFL Live, and sharing your insights.
Best of luck to you this coming season.
- Appreciate it, thank you for having me.
- All right, so back to our declarations
if you weren't here earlier.
Tomorrow's the Fourth of
July and the anniversary
of the Declaration of Independence.
So we're making some
NFL declarations today,
here on NFL Live.
Earlier, Damien made a
declaration about Kirk Cousins.
He was very vociferous.
Mike, you got one on the Jaguars?
- I absolutely do.
I declare that Nick Foles will
lead the Jacksonville Jaguars
to the Super Bowl representing the AFC.
And I know that you know
this because you're a student
of the game, but last
year, in division games,
the Jacksonville Jaguars averaged less
than 10 points a game.
You take what is already a
championship-level defense,
led by Jalen Ramsey, and this year's
first round pick, Josh Allen
with a quarterback who won
a Super Bowl two years ago,
and but for a drop in the
last year's NFC playoffs,
may have brought the Eagles to
two consecutive Super Bowls,
so that's my declaration.
- This is interesting because
Jalen Ramsey has, in fact,
stayed on the line and
heard your declaration,
Mike Tannebaum.
So Jalen, I'm curious
what your thoughts are
on Mike's declaration about the Jaguars.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I love that declaration right there.
Speak it into existence for us, I love it.
I'm super excited to
have Nick on the team,
and we're gonna put all
that confidence behind him,
and we're gonna let him lead the offense.
And like you said, this defense we have,
we think some big things could be in store
for the 2019 season.
- So Jalen, when everybody else is getting
on that Jaguar bandwagon
come the regular season,
just remember we had this
conversation on July 3rd,
and that was my declaration.
So I'm with you guys, the
bandwagon starts today.
Let's not let anybody else on.
- Thanks, Jalen.
- I got you.
- [Dan] We appreciate you sticking around.
- Appreciate y'all.
- Love it.
That declaration, we should have Jalen in,
and he could do his declaration.
- So you just go all in on
my head about Kirk Cousins,
but you all in on Jacksonville.
Listen, Nick Foles was
great with Doug Peterson.
It seems like they had a chemistry.
So you think they can
recreate that in Jacksonville
with this whole different
cast of characters?
- No doubt about it, and as you know,
it starts with the offensive line.
They have a very good offensive line.
They added Jawaan Taylor at
right tackle, who's gonna start.
Doug Marrone was an offensive
lineman, played, coached it,
and now he's their head coach.
And it allows them to travel,
play well on the road.
And with that defense,
they're loaded up front.
They have a lot of depth at pass rusher,
when you look at last
year's first round pick,
Tavon Bryant, (stammering).
- Ngakoue?
- Ngakoue, yes, at defensive end.
And Calais Campbell, and
again Josh Allen this year.
I think they have depth up front.
They have two cover corners in AJ Bouye,
and Jalen Ramsey, you saw.
I think they're really built well.
And now you have
below-average quarterback play
in Blake Bortles, and we're
being generous with that.
And Nick Foles is a good quarterback,
so that's my declaration.
- I'll tell you one big difference,
and that might be the
reason they sign him.
Foles only threw 23
interceptions in 40 games
in Philadelphia, Bortles
had 58 interceptions
in 60 games with the Jaguars.
So they should be better there.
We're gonna have more
declarations later in the show.
We're also gonna talk some soccer.
Alex Morgan shook up the Twitterverse
with her tea sipping goal celebration
that Jalen Ramsey enjoyed.
Which celebrations from
NFL history compare
to this surprisingly controversial one?
Stay tuned to NFL Live,
we'll talk about it.
(exciting music)
- [Narrator] Why use
Post-It Extreme Notes?
Because they make your message stick.
Getting it said and done
right the first time.
- [Man in Jacket] Oh, come on!
- [Narrator] Stop the re-work
with Post-it Extreme Notes.
(lifeguard whistle blowing)
- Not running!
Why am I not running?
Because the DQ Summer Blizzard menu
is only here for a few more
weeks with seven great flavors,
like new Sour Patch
Kids and Brownie Dough.
(lifeguard whistle blows)
- Not running!
- [Narrator] DQ, Happy tastes good.
(bell ringing)
- Hi.
- (chuckles) We all just got
new smartphones at Cricket.
- Hi.
- Hola.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
- [Narrator] Is Bud Light
Orange coming back this summer
and never leaving?
And brewed with real orange peels?
The answer is yes.
Yes, and yes.
(funky music)
- Nice on, Mallory.
(cheering)
- What's this?
- Oh, it's their new goal celebration.
They're calling it the
Hulu-has-live-sports.
You've got your standard
issue couch, and they're a TV.
- How much is Hulu paying them for this?
- Hulu has live sports.
♪ Summer nights keeping me up ♪
♪ I wanna waste time just looking up ♪
♪ Sky full of stars mind wandering far ♪
♪ Like we're 16 dreaming in the dark ♪
♪ Love the wind in my
hair as I drive my car ♪
♪ Makes me feel free ♪
- [Narrator] Now, get exceptional offers
at the Infiniti Plus Summer Sales Event.
- [Narrator] In every
trip, there's room for more
than just the business you came for.
Whether that's keeping up
with what you always do,
or training for something
you've never done before.
That's room for possibility.
- [Narrator] If you're thinking
about buying a new home,
here's some great news.
Mortgage interest rates have dropped.
This means right now is a
perfect time to save money
when you're ready to buy a new home.
But even if you're not ready
to buy quite yet, that's okay.
At Quicken Loans, we
believe you should be able
to benefit from a great rate before you
even begin your home search.
That's why Quicken Loans
created our exclusive
RateShield Approval.
It's designed to protect
you from unpredictable
interest rates.
Here's how our RateShield Approval works.
First, we lock your interest
rate for up to 90 days
while you find your new home.
Then, once you've found your new home,
if rates have gone up,
your low rate stays locked.
But if rates have gone
down, your rate drops,
and you get to keep that new, lower rate.
Remember, mortgage interest
rates are low right now,
and that's great, but you
never know when they may rise
So protect yourself, and take the worry
out of unpredictable interest rates
with a RateShield Approval,
exclusively from Quicken Loans.
If you're thinking about buying a home,
call Quicken Loans, or go
to RocketMortgage.com today.
- Big welcome to all my
first time Peloton riders.
Keep it up, Peloton.
Let's be better than we were yesterday.
Let's go, come on.
(cheerful music)
- [Narrator] Milestones
that keep you coming back.
- Janet's in for 100 rides for you today.
- [Narrator] Just one part of the
best cardio machine on the planet
Peloton.
- [Narrator] Exclusively
on ESPN Plus, UFC 239.
After a successful UFC debut,
two-time collegiate wrestling
champion, Ben Askren,
looks to stay undefeated
as he sets his sights
on a title shot.
Buy it on ESPNplus.com/PPV.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Don't go anywhere just yet!
- With the first pick,
the New Orleans Pelicans
select Zion Williamson.
The New York Knicks select RJ Barrett.
- I love the biggest stage,
I love the challenge.
- My dreams came true,
I'm just ready to work.
- [Dan] NBA Summer League action, Friday.
We've got a triple-header
starting at 7:30 Eastern
on ESPN, and you won't want to miss
that special matchup at 9:30 Eastern Time
featuring former Duke teammates,
Zion Williamson and RJ Barrett facing off
for the first time as pros.
Speaking of the NBA,
Lakers fan Damien Woody
insists that we talk
about the Kawhi Leonard
free agency situation.
Still waiting for word from
Kawhi on where he'll end up.
But if it is the Lakers, Damien's excited
to see that picture right there.
- That's right, that's right.
- Would form an imposing big three
with LeBron James and Anthony Davis.
So, I feel like I've said
this about 20 times today.
That got us thinking.
- Got us thinking.
- About NFL big threes, and we're looking
at some pretty good ones right here.
Mike Tannenbaum, why don't
you rank them for us.
Count them down starting five to one.
- All right, number five, I'm gonna go
with the LA Rams, staying
in LA, with come on over.
- There you go.
- There we go.
- Jared Goff, Brendan
Cooks, and Todd Gurley.
The reason why they're only
five is while I like Cooks,
I don't see him as an elite receiver.
He's straight-line,
he's fast, but not great
at changing direction, so
that's why they're five for me.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Got them to the Super Bowl.
- Number four, the Atlanta Falcons.
You look at Matt Ryan,
Super Bowl quarterback,
Julio Jones, arguably the
best receiver in the NFL.
And then, obviously, Freeman
coming off the injury,
but he's a good running back.
So, I think that's a really
solid three guys right there.
- Both of those running
backs coming off of injury.
Their seasons could really
rest on those two guys
to some extent, right?
- [Damien] Absolutely,
and you know, the Falcons,
they drafted a couple of linemen up front,
so it should be good news for Matt Ryan
and Devonta Freeman.
- Always the linemen, huh?
- Yeah, that's right.
- We should have done big
three offensive linemen.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Cowboy and whatever else.
- Number three, the Dallas Cowboys.
- Hey.
- A lot of people don't realize this,
but Dak Prescott, 32-16 as
a starting NFL quarterback.
Ezekiel Elliott, arguably
as good a running back
as there is in the league.
And Amari Cooper, all they did last year
was go 7-2 after the trade.
And they were number one
over the last nine games
on third down.
- [Dan] Number two, what have you got?
- Okay, the New Orleans Saints, led by
future Hall of Famer,
Drew Brees at quarterback.
- [Dan] Heard of him.
- Michael Thomas, who is.
- He's not bad.
- Who is not bad, right maybe
a tick below Julio Jones,
and not far behind him, Alvin Kumara.
And what I love about Kumara is not only
is he a great running back, but he's great
out of the backfield as a receiver.
And he puts so much pressure
on other teams' defense.
- [Dan] Who could be better than that?
I'm a little surprised
that's not number one.
- Yeah let's see, Mike.
- Who you got at number one?
- One of your former teams.
- Oh, okay.
- The New England Patriots.
As someone that's been in
the AFC East for 20 years,
trying to compete with these guys.
Tom Brady, best quarterback of all-time.
Julian Edelman, I have so
much respect and admiration
for him, college quarterback,
he has rolled himself
into a great player.
And look, Sony Michel is
the player that Zeke Elliott
or Alvin Kumara is, but
he was a first round pick,
he got better as the year went on.
If he can overcome a knee injury,
he's gonna turn into being
a good NFL running back.
But, Tom Brady, it starts with him.
- You know, Mike, I'm so
disappointed in you right now.
- You know why, you left off my
Minnesota Vikings right here.
I don't know why you don't
believe in Kirk Cousins.
Obviously, this might be
the best duo in the league
in Adam Thielen, and Stefon Diggs.
What is up with the hate
against the Minnesota Vikings?
You need to explain yourself to all
the purple people-eaters out there.
- I watched the tape, that's why.
(laughing)
- Whoa!
- All right, all right.
- That is a good group.
I'm not saying it's not
likewise with Pittsburgh,
and obviously Kansas City.
These are all good, but
you're talking about
a Hall of Fame quarterback in Tom Brady,
Hall of Fame quarterback in Drew Brees.
You look at Dallas, look, Matt Ryan,
certainly has a Hall of
Fame credentials, possibly.
And I think that five
is a really high-level.
Nothing to be ashamed of over
here, but not in the top five.
- Do you think that if Dalvin Cook
is a healthy running back this year,
he could be good enough to put them
in this kind of category?
- Boy, that's a really good question.
I think Dalvin Cook is a game-changer.
Kirk Cousins is at best
with a good running game,
good offensive line, play action.
And Dalvin Cook could hopefully not only
help the running game,
but their passing game.
- Those are our big threes.
Still nothing on Kawhi,
sorry, we'll let you know
if we hear anything, but in the meantime,
we're gonna talk to Browns
tight end, David Njoku,
about all the good stuff coming
up this year in Cleveland.
(exciting music)
(somber piano music)
- What's up DK?
I know you're asking
yourself, am I worth the hype?
- [Announcer] Are you kidding me?
Why we love the combine.
- Can I live up to it all?
See, that's the thing about hype.
It can make you, or break you.
And here's what I've learned,
they get to ask all the questions,
but only you get to answer.
- [Announcer] The Seattle
Seahawks select DK Metcalf.
(cheering)
- [Larry] Good luck, DK.
- [Narrator] New for summer.
Here for summer, arriving this summer.
It's Bud Light Lemon Tea.
New for summer.
(suspenseful music)
- I've waited my whole life for this.
- You ready?
- Are you?
(dramatic music)
(cheering)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Look, make a wish.
- I wish for a Biggie Bag from Wendy's.
- I wish everyone loves
each other, and was all--
- That was a great wish, Jimmy.
- [Narrator] Get a Bacon Double Stack
with a quarter pound of fresh beef,
nuggets, fries, and a
drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
- [Narrator] When you
need hot or cold therapy
for strained or injured muscles.
Don't give up your freedom
to get your therapy.
Get that healing feeling with Copper Fit
Mobile Rapid Relief Wraps.
Hot or cold therapy
wraps that strap in place
and stay in place, so
you can do what you want
while getting the therapy you need.
- This is the best solution
for icing and heating
that I've ever found.
- [Narrator] Get that healing feeling
with Copper Fit Rapid Relief Wraps.
Find the entire line of Copper
Fit Rapid Relief Mobile Wraps
now in Walmart Pharmacy.
- Bro.
- (gasps) I got this.
- Bros?
- Bro?
(bell dinging)
- Bro.
(cheerful music)
- Bro!
- Bro?
- Bro.
- Oh, bro.
(groaning)
- Bro!
- Bro.
- Later, Bromies.
- Bros?
- Bro!
- [Narrator] Stuber, in theaters.
- [Narrator] I bet you've
never seen a bed like this.
It's the New Craftmatic
Legacy Rising Pillow Rest
Adjustable Bed.
Featuring bedside power
plugs, under-bed night lights
and more for less, up to 50 percent less
than Tempur-Pedic, Sleep
Number and other adjustables.
Call now, you gotta see
how little they cost.
- All right, we're in
this together, Peloton.
Three, two, rise with me!
Make every step a little
stronger than the last.
- [Narrator] Over 90
live classes every week.
Just one part of the best cardio machine
on the planet, Peloton.
- Tired of lugging around big
bags of pet food and litter?
Get it delivered.
Chewy.com delivers
everything your pets need
right to your door.
They ship all your favorite brands
of dog food, cat food,
litter, toys, and treats.
All at amazing prices.
Start saving today.
Plus, you get fast free shipping.
(doorbell ringing)
With Chewy.com, you don't have
to break a sweat or the bank.
Save 30 percent off on your first order,
and get fast free shipping.
Shop online at Chewy.com.
- Breaking news into NFL Live.
Cowboys running back, Ezekiel
Elliott has been informed
he will not be suspended for his role
in that recent altercation in Las Vegas
with the security guard that we discussed
at the top of the show.
Elliott met with Commissioner
Roger Goodell yesterday,
and issued a statement last night
about his involvement there, apologizing.
And we are now being
informed that he will not
face another suspension.
So obviously a relief for Ezekiel Elliott,
and for the Cowboys there.
- Yeah, absolutely, listen as
a veteran in the locker room,
this is exactly the
outcome that you wanted.
You want all your guys, all
hands on deck to be available.
This is an important year for everyone
within the Dallas Cowboys organization
from the head coach on down.
And obviously, maybe the
most important player
for their team is going to be available
at the start of the season.
- [Dan] You surprised, Mike?
- I was mildly surprised, because again,
the personal conduct
policy's standard is lower
than criminal conduct.
So, the commissioner could
have suspended the player,
especially because he's a repeat offender.
And the fact that he
brought him to New York City
shows that it was significant enough
for a face to face meeting.
And look, at the end
of the day, hopefully,
Ezekiel Elliott has learned,
and all these sort of
bumps in the road he's
had from off the field
are in his past, because
he is a great player,
and by all accounts, he's
a good teammate as well.
So hopefully, he's learned
from this and he's moved on.
- [Dan] We talked earlier
in the show about the kind
of conversation you have with
a player in this situation
if you're the front office.
Does the fact that he
isn't being suspended
change any part of that message or make it
even more difficult to deliver?
- No, you have to have a stern, direct,
and a very hard conversation
that your behavior
is not acceptable.
And even though it didn't
rise to level of suspension,
it's still not conduct
becoming of a Dallas Cowboy.
And again, if I was in the front
office, making the decision
I would hit pause on
the contract extension.
And I would put my efforts and
energy into the good players
and the players that have
handled themselves the right way
off the field, starting
with the quarterback,
Dak Prescott, and their
receiver Amari Cooper.
So, hopefully, it's a lesson
learned for Ezekiel Elliott,
it doesn't happen again.
But if I'm the Dallas
Cowboys, I have to have
that conversation with him and
tell him what we're thinking,
and why we're thinking it.
- Damien?
- Again, as a player in the locker room,
you just, this is what you wanted to hear.
That he's gonna be available,
and we can go out here
and win some football games.
- But I mean, is there
anything to the idea,
like he's not being
suspended, so you still have
to sort of make sure that something
is learned from this, right, as a player?
- Well, I mean that's something
for the Dallas Cowboys,
maybe internally as an
organization they want to do,
but for a veteran, don't
mess with my money.
That's my biggest thing
is when you're not there,
you affect my play, so let's
stay on the straight and narrow
so we can go out here and
win some football games.
- Not that this necessarily
ever happened to you,
but do you think being called
into the commissioner's office
even if it doesn't result in punishment
is enough to get the message across?
- Yeah, it should be like a
Scared Straight, you know.
Like, you gotta fly
all the way to New York
to go talk to big bad Roger Goodell.
You would think like, okay, all right,
let me make sure I'm on the
straight and narrow here.
So hopefully, Zeke Elliott
has learned from this,
and the Dallas Cowboys as an organization
can move forward now.
- I think that's the part
that there's a lot of people
in the NFL community that
are surprised about it,
because that's what happened
the last time two years ago.
Got suspended, had to
go to the league office,
and you would think,
especially with the contract
on the horizon, that he would really try
to be impeccable off the field.
But again, hopefully he's learned from it,
he can move on, and put this behind him.
- Lot of expectations for
the Cowboys this year.
Obviously, this clears the decks in terms
of one major concern.
They have some contract
situations to work through
as they head into camp,
but you see this as a team
that's primed for a real
serious run this time?
- I think the Dallas Cowboys can represent
the NFC in the Super Bowl.
I think this team, the way
that Dak Prescott played
after the trade of Amari
Cooper from Oakland,
the numbers speak for themselves.
Across the board, completion percentage,
yards per attempt, third down.
All those numbers were
significantly better
with Amari Cooper.
Doing a trade during
the season, so imagine
now in the offseason, obviously you've got
a new offensive coordinator
in Kellen Moore.
We don't know how that's
going to all work out,
but you think that he's gonna accentuate
all the different aspects of Dak's game.
This offense, this team in general to me,
is one of the better teams in
the National Football League.
- [Dan] Only three teams in
the league have won more games
than the Cowboys have
over the last three years.
That's the Chiefs, the
Patriots, and the Steelers.
That's pretty good company.
- Yeah, and again, I
don't think Dak Prescott
gets enough credit,
he's 32-16 as a starter.
The ultimate measure of a
quarterback is win-loss record.
And you go back to last
year, he had a pass rating
of 122 on play action plays.
So, it shows you the
importance of Ezekiel Elliott's
availability, as you mentioned, Damien.
So, depending on the
health of Carson Wentz,
I think Dallas has a
really reasonable chance
of winning this division.
Over the last couple
of years, Philadelphia
has done such a good job of
having depth behind Wentz
with Nick Foles.
Foles isn't there anymore,
Nate Sudfeld is going
to be their presumptive
backup quarterback.
So, Wentz has to overcome that issue.
Can he stay healthy for 16 games?
And you look at the way
Dallas has built this team
on both sides of the ball that I think
they'll be right there with Philly
going down the stretch here.
- So the NFL has released
a statement on this issue
regarding Ezekiel Elliott,
announcing that he
won't be suspended and it reads like this.
"Immediately following reports
of an incident in Las Vegas
"in May involving Ezekiel
Elliott of the Dallas Cowboys,
"the NFL conducted a
comprehensive investigation
"that included interviews
with multiple witnesses,
"including security personnel and others
"with direct involvement,
as well as a review
"of documentary and other information.
"On Tuesday, as part of the
review, NFL Commissioner
"Roger Goodell met with
Mr. Elliott to reinforce
"the standards of conduct expected of him,
"and the consequences for
failing to meet those standards.
"Mr. Elliott acknowledged
that he demonstrated
"poor judgment and committed
to make better choices
"in the future.
"He volunteered to take
advantage of the resources
"available to him to help him
continue to grow personally.
"Commissioner Goodell determined
there was no violation
"of the personal conduct policy,
"and no further action is warranted."
So the statement confirming
what we were told,
any quick reactions there?
- He got lucky.
I mean, he could have
easily, he could've easily
been suspended again.
You know, Mike, you had
touched upon it prior,
but usually in these situations,
this is your second time going to New York
to talk to the commissioner,
you've already been suspended
before and you get off with no punishment.
He's very fortunate to
be in this situation.
- Something else that they
touched on the letter there
is that the league and
the union both deserve
a lot of credit for is the
resources that are available
to players, to coaches,
to staff in terms of
if you feel like you need help.
And there are a lot of
resources behind the scenes,
and hopefully if he needs
that, that he takes advantage
of it and I know they
mentioned that in the letter,
and that's an important aspect
of the collective bargaining agreement.
And that's an example of the partnership
between the league and
the union where they are
trying to help players.
- So once again, the news
on Cowboys running back
Ezekiel Elliott, no
punishment, no suspension
as a result of his most recent incident.
When we return on NFL Live, Alex Morgan
woke up social media after
casually sipping her tea Tuesday.
We'll show you some NFL celebrations
that Alex reminded us of.
- They want a show,
they're about to get one.
It's the T.O. show right now.
We got your popcorn ready.
Get your popcorn ready.
(stammering) That's all folks.
(exciting music)
- Speaking here from the New York Times.
(tense music)
- Hey, you see this?
- Holy.
- [Narrator] This is Payday bar.
And there's only one thing
you need to know about it.
It has a truckload of peanuts
surrounding sweet caramel.
I mean, holy.
(drill buzzing)
Look at all those peanuts.
The best part is, it helps
you get through your day.
Payday, get to it.
♪ Summer nights keeping me up ♪
♪ I wanna waste time just looking up ♪
♪ Sky full of stars mind wandering far ♪
♪ Like we're 16 dreaming in the dark ♪
♪ Got the wind in my
hair as I drive my car ♪
♪ It makes me feel free ♪
- [Narrator] Now, get exceptional offers
at the Infiniti Plus Summer Sales Event.
- [Narrator] You can tell
from the airborne citrus
that Bud Light Lime, Orange, and Lemon Tea
are brewed with real lime,
orange, and lemon peels.
Or maybe you can't,
but there are some firm context clues.
(funky music)
- [Narrator] In every
trip, there's room for more
than just the business you came for.
Whether that's taking in every moment,
or capturing a moment worth bringing back.
That's room for possibility.
- [Narrator] Feed your imagination.
Feed your excitement.
Feed your hunger.
When heroes get hungry, they get
the $12 Extra Large Superhero
Pizza at Papa John's.
(doorbell rings)
- It's open.
- Hi.
This is amazing.
- [Narrator] With moderate
to severe ulcerative colitis.
- Are you okay?
- [Narrator] Even when I was there,
I never knew when my
symptoms would keep us apart.
So, I talked to my doctor about Humira.
I learned Humira can help
get and keep UC under control
when other medications
haven't worked well enough.
And it helps people
achieve control that lasts,
so you can experience few or no symptoms.
- [Narrator] Humira can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems.
Serious allergic reactions and new
or worsening heart failure.
Before treatment, get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common.
And if you've had TB, hepatitis
B, are prone to infections,
or have flu-like symptoms or sores,
don't start Humira if
you have an infection.
- [Narrator] Be there for you and them.
Ask your gastroenterologist about Humira.
With Humira, control is possible.
- The only thing we
love more than Slinging.
- Is showing folks how easy it is.
- You got a good grip, bro,
explore all the possibilities.
- Oh, Sling TV.
- Your first time Slinging
is always so special.
- I cried my first time.
- Nick is a very generous Slinger.
- I like to share.
- [Narrator] Stop paying too much for TV.
For a limited time, get all your favorite
live TV channels, only 15
bucks for your first month
at SlingTV.com.
- [Narrator] What does
it mean to be an American
playing at Wimbledon?
It means following in the footsteps
of some of the best to ever play here.
It means wearing white but
dream red, white, and blue.
It means being part of a
new generation of Americans
looking to light their
own Wimbledon history.
The story continues.
The Championships, Wimbledon.
July 4th coverage begins
at 6 a.m. on ESPN.
- [Narrator] Keep up with
your favorite team on the go
with the NFL app.
Get all your updates,
scores and live games
during the season.
Download the NFL app, from your app store.
- The ESPYS auction is where you can bid
on a once in a lifetime experiences,
like joining me on the
set of Sportscenter.
That should be like a million dollars.
- Join me in Sunday Night
Baseball in the booth.
- You can join me, and we'll
make a puppet in your likeness.
- Come hang out with me
and my least favorite
son, Dan, on South Beach.
- [Scott] So bid now, at Ebay.com/ESPN.
- As Scott said, the
ESPYS auction includes
amazing experiences across
sports and entertainment,
including these incredible
football experiences.
Go to Ebay.com/ESPN to
bid now to July 10th.
All proceeds benefit the V
Foundation for cancer research.
If you weren't with us
in the last segment,
we did have breaking
news on Ezekiel Elliott,
the running back for the Dallas Cowboys.
The league has announced that
he will not face a punishment
for his role in a recent
incident in Las Vegas
involving a security guard.
The commissioner found he did not violate
the personal conduct policy,
so no suspension for Elliott.
Much more on that throughout
the day here on ESPN.
Big news yesterday in the
other kind of football
was the US Women's soccer
team beating England
in the semifinals of the World Cup.
Since that team can't seem to do anything
without people finding a
reason to criticize it.
Part of the story has become Alex Morgan's
tea-sipping celebration
following what turned out
to be the game-winning goal.
The criticism seems to center on the idea
that the celebration was
directed at the opponent,
which was England.
But however you feel about
it, it got us thinking
about situations in the
NFL where people celebrate,
and kind of tailor their celebrations
a little bit to the opponent.
Week four, the year is
2000, 49ers and Cowboys.
Terrell Owens celebrates a touchdown
by posing on the Dallas star.
Was that aimed at the
Cowboys, I couldn't tell.
(laughing)
- [Damien] I love it, man, I love it.
- [Dan] 2018, Week 10, Dolphins-Packers,
Packers Robert Quinn sacks Aaron Rodgers,
and mocks him with the old
Discount Double Check celebration.
- [Damien] If you're gonna dish it,
you gotta be able to take it.
- Come home to roost.
- Right.
- [Dan] We got Baker Mayfield.
Oklahoma, this is college
footage of Baker Mayfield.
Oklahoma-Ohio State, OU
defeats the Buckeyes,
and Baker plants the OU
flag on the Ohio State logo
at midfield, again not real subtle.
2011 NFC Wild Card game, I
was there, Falcons-Giants.
Hakeem Nicks catches
a long touchdown pass,
and celebrates by doing
the Falcons signature
Dirty Bird Dance.
I thought Hakeem was too
young to even know that dance.
(laughing)
Did his research before
the game, I like that.
Week 10, 2012,
Panthers-Broncos, Von Miller
sacks Cam Newton and
does Newton's signature
Superman celebration.
(laughing)
Von, a little takeoff after that.
He practiced that.
- [Damien] That's right,
you go into these games,
you have them dialed up ready to go.
- [Mike] Oh, yeah got
a little strut there.
- [Damien] That's right, that's right.
- How about TO again?
Week 8, 2004, Eagles-Ravens,
Terrell Owens catches
a touchdown pass, then celebrates
with Ray Lewis's signature pregame dance.
- [Mike] Oh he got it, oh that's good.
- [Damien] I love TO, man.
- [Dan] Impersonated it before,
but that's as good as it gets.
- [Damien] If you don't
wanna see him do it,
then you better stop him, I always say.
- You know he practiced that.
- Of course.
Listen, that stuff, while
you front office guys
are up in your office or whatever,
these guys are sitting in the locker room,
they're thinking of all types
of things to do on gameday,
so I love it, man.
- [Dan] Did you know that's what they were
doing down there while
you were in your office?
- They were studying film?
- Come on, man, don't be a lame.
Look, we're trying to have fun out here.
This is a sport, we're trying to have fun.
- Look, the NFL has allowed
some celebrations recently,
but they still don't like the
direct taunting of opponents.
Where's the line?
- (sighs) Listen, for me it's competition.
It's competition for me.
I know everyone's gonna
talk about sportsmanship.
Obviously, I'm a proponent
of sportsmanship,
but I've always been under the impression
that if you don't want
people to celebrate,
if you don't want people
to talk trash, stop them.
Stop them, plain and simple.
- Oh man.
- And for me, you know when
they celebrate as a team,
it's great, and the last couple of years,
there have been some very
creative celebrations.
Last year, going back to the
Steelers they're bench pressing
so to me when it's the
team, I'm all for it.
- Spoken like a true general manager.
(laughing)
- Up in his office while you guys are all
practicing your celebrations
in the locker room.
Coming up on NFL Live,
we're gonna have much more
on the Ezekiel Elliott situation.
Cowboys running back not
suspended by the league
after his recent meeting with
Commissioner Roger Goodell.
We'll come back and
talk about it some more,
next on NFL Live.
(exciting music)
- Let me get this straight,
after a long day of hard work,
you have to do more work?
Everyday, you're nearly fried
to a crisp professionally.
Can someone turn on the AC?
No? All right.
Because there isn't any.
Here.
- [Narrator] Automatically
sort your expenses
and save over 40 hours a month.
- Without you, we
wouldn't have electricity.
Our hobby would be going to be early.
- [Narrator] You earned it, we're here
to make sure you get it.
- It's time to get yours.
- [Narrator] QuickBooks, backing you.
(sizzling)
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Tecate, bold on the outside,
light on the inside.
(whistle blows)
- Not running.
Why am I "not running"?
Because the DQ Summer
Blizzard Menu's only here
for a few more weeks
with seven great flavors,
like new Sour Patch
Kids, and Brownie Dough.
(whistle blows)
- Not running!
- [Narrator] DQ, happy tastes good.
- [Narrator] The ant,
mindlessly marches on,
carrying up to 50 times its body weight.
It never questions the task at hand.
But this year, there's another more
thrilling path to follow.
- Kids?
(dramatic music)
(engine whirring)
Change of plans.
- [Narrator] Defy the laws of human nature
at the Summer of Audi Sales Event.
Get exceptional offers now.
- If something happened to
you, what would happen to them?
Their home, their education, their future?
You need life insurance.
And chances are Select
Quote can help you get it
for less than a dollar a day.
- [Narrator] Select Quote found Jacob, 40,
a $500,000 policy for only $19 a month.
And Select Quote found his wife, Wendy,
a $500,000 policy for only $17 a month.
- Our secret?
At Select Quote, we
aggressively comparison shop
up to 10 highly-rated
companies to find you
the company with the best rates.
- [Narrator] We found Gary,
35, a one million dollar policy
for only $22 a month.
- Why pay more?
Give your family the security they need
at a price you can afford.
- [Narrator] Call 1-800-394-8946,
or go to SelectQuote.com
now and get the insurance
your family needs.
- At a price you can afford.
Select Quote, we shop, you save.
(solemn piano music)
- What's good, Josh, this is Deshaun.
Man, I know what you're going through.
You know, sometimes you get a great hand.
And the other times, you don't.
Living in your dad's
car, always on the move?
You played the hand you had,
and it paid off.
- [Announcer] Lowers
the shoulder and scores.
- [Deshaun] And the cards are
about to be dealt again, Josh.
- The Oakland Raiders select Josh Jacobs.
- [Deshaun] This is your time, my dog.
- [Narrator] Personal training
just got a lot more personal.
- Good morning, from Bora Bora.
- [Narrator] Introducing
the all-new X Series
from NordicTrack.
- You ready to get started
on today's workout, let's go.
- [Narrator] All you have
to do is press start.
- So glad you could join me this morning.
Let's go!
- [Narrator] Your trainer
controls the speed.
- We'll take it up to 60 percent.
- [Narrator] Incline,
decline, and duration
of your workout.
This is what results in your
home, on your terms looks like.
You can take advantage of our
special 36 month financing
for qualified buyers.
Only at NordicTrack.com
(solemn chiming music)
- Recapping our breaking
news today on NFL Live.
Cowboys running back
Ezekiel Elliott will not
face punishment for his
role in a recent incident
with a security guard in Las Vegas.
Elliott met with
Commissioner Roger Goodell
for a couple of hours Tuesday of this week
and was informed he
would not be suspended.
The NFL released a statement explaining it
basically says that they
found he did not violate
the personal conduct policy, but they hope
that he continues to stay
out of these situations
in the future, Damien
what are your thoughts?
- Well I mean, my biggest thing
is does Zeke grow from here?
This is the second time going to New York.
First time was, I believe it
was a six-game suspension.
This time, obviously, he
got off with no suspension,
but you would think
that at this point now,
it's time for you to grow and mature,
and not put yourself in
compromising situations,
because again, as a veteran,
I'm depending on you.
Guys in the locker room
need all hands on deck,
so I just want to see
more growth and maturity
out of Zeke Elliott.
- I totally agree, and you
take that a step further
with the contract situation.
If he's behaving like
this without that big deal
that Todd Gurley deal with
$45 million guarantee.
You know from an organization standpoint,
what is he gonna be like
once he has that money?
So, not only do I have pause
for concern to doing a deal,
but if and when we get to that point,
now I really gonna make
sure that the structure
is appropriate where
we'll guarantee money,
certainly if he gets
hurt playing football,
but beyond that, we're gonna
want to have the ability
to move on from the
player if there's a third
bump in the road in terms
of something happening
off the field, so he's put
himself in that position.
And again, he's had
some teammates that have
played very well, like
the starting quarterback
Dak Prescott and have handled
their business off the field.
So, he's done this to himself, so not only
would I consider pausing and
not doing a long-term deal
if and when we got to that point.
The structure of the contract would be,
I want the player to take the risk,
because as an organization,
if something else happens
I want to be able to cut the player
and not have to pay him any more money.
- That's a key point, if
something else happens.
He was warned the last time
when he was suspended in 2017.
And he seems to, as Damien said earlier,
maybe he got lucky this
time, because they certainly
could have suspended him again
under the personal conduct
policy, given that warning.
But this is a transcendent
player who has led the league
in rushing two of his three years.
Led the league in rushing yards per game
the year he was suspended.
To get to the point where you release him,
that has to be a pretty
extreme situation, doesn't it?
- Well listen, we all
know how the league works.
The more talented you are as a player,
the more opportunities you're gonna get.
And you said it perfectly,
he's a transcendent talent.
One of the best players
that we have in our league.
But again, if you're not available,
what good are you to the team?
So again, you would
like to see Zeke Elliott
mature and get past these incidences
that we've seen from him.
The three years plus or whatever he's been
in the National Football League,
so he can help his team
get to where they wanna go
which is to the Super Bowl.
- That's right, the old
saying in pro football,
production equals tolerance.
And because he's produced
such a high level,
there's been a high level of tolerance.
But at some point, that's gonna equal out,
and hopefully he can
learn from this, grow,
and put all this behind
him and help the Cowboys
try to win a Super Bowl.
- Ezekiel Elliott represents
the big NFL news of the day.
On ESPN though, we don't
limit ourselves to NFL.
Our next Canadian Football
League matchup on ESPN Plus
is tomorrow night, it's
a week four matchup
between the 3-0 Hamilton Tiger-Cats,
and the Montreal Alouettes.
Looking for their first win of the season.
That'll be at 7:30 Eastern.
- Everybody's gonna say that we could be
and should be Super Bowl contenders.
- Who wouldn't aspire to be the Patriots?
Who wouldn't want to be 11-5, 12-4 team?
- I want to get there,
so we can print that.
I want to get to be what the Patriots are.
- [Damien] The Cleveland
Browns are going from
the hunter to the hunted now.
- [Announcer] Oh, what a
catch by Njoku, touchdown.
- I said I woke up feeling dangerous, son.
- I'm almost giddy.
I feel like a little kid,
the excitement that I have.
(screaming)
- [Mike] They have no excuse
for not being a contender
in the AFC to go to the Super Bowl.
They have no excuse.
- Cleveland Browns tight end,
David Njoku joins us now.
Getting ready for a highly-anticipated
season in Cleveland.
David, we've seen some
of what you guys can do,
certainly individually,
but what we haven't seen
is Freddie Kitchens as a head coach.
So tell us, what's Freddie like
now that he's the head coach?
- Freddie's a great head
coach, I believe, you know.
He's a player's coach
if that makes any sense.
You know, he knows what it takes for us
to do what we have to
do, and we know as well.
We put everything together, and hopefully
good things will happen,
you know, so we'll see.
- Bringing some stability
to that situation this year,
and obviously last year there wasn't.
What was it like going
through that last year
with all the turmoil and the firings
and all that stuff that happened midseason
with the coaching staff
changes, how tough was that?
- Yes, you know it was a
bunch of turmoil, you know.
Obviously, having your head coach fired,
and your OC also fired.
It brought a lot of
questions and the curiosity.
But, I feel like as a
team and the players,
we took it upon ourselves to come together
and focus on how we have
to finish this year,
or this past year, strong.
And I believe we did just that, you know.
I believe this upcoming year
is gonna be real special, so.
- A lot of times players say that stuff,
the front office stuff, coaching stuff
doesn't have an effect in the locker room,
but were there hard feelings?
It seemed like when you
guys ran into Cincinnati,
Baker Mayfield, your
quarterback had some things
to say about the situation.
Was that a widespread feeling?
- There's no hard feelings
at the end of the day.
Everyone must understand
that this is a business,
and you have to treat it as such.
So, there is no hard feelings, you know.
Whatever happened
happened, it is what it is.
And now we're focused
on what we have to do
to reach our goal this year.
- Obviously, you guys
did not lack for talent
on the offensive side of
the ball to begin with,
but Odell Beckham established as really
one of the top receiving
options in the entire league.
What have you seen from him in terms
of what he's shown you on the field,
and what kind of teammate he is?
- Yeah, so Odell is an elite athlete.
We were actually all together yesterday.
Jarvis, Hollywood Higgins, me, Baker,
and a bunch of other guys,
Seth DeValve, Demetrius
Harris, Pharaoh Brown,
together working on timing and everything.
So when it comes to us as a unit,
we're very dangerous is the word to say.
- Yeah, how about personal goals for you?
Obviously, you know, you're a young player
who's still growing in this league.
What do you look at and
say, here's what I want
to accomplish this year and going forward?
- As long as I feel that I gave it my all,
I work to my highest
ability, then I'm content
with this year.
I don't really have any numbers.
I was messing around saying 20 touchdowns,
but honestly speaking, I just
want to have a great year.
We want to win as many games as possible,
and we want to, obviously, go
to the Super Bowl and win it.
So that's the big term goal.
- When you're looking
to improve your game,
is there something you're
specifically working on
this offseason that you're
trying to get better at?
- Oh yeah, of course, I
mean honestly speaking,
I'm working on all aspects.
I don't believe I've mastered anything
regarding the tight end position just yet,
so it's really just
everything I want to work on
to better myself as an
overall tight end and player.
- I wanted to ask you a personal question,
if that's all right.
You have eight siblings, is that correct?
You're one of nine brothers and sisters?
- Correct.
- Your older brother, Innocent, studying
to be a neurologist.
What kinds of conversations--
- Neurosurgeon.
- Oh, neurosurgeon, excuse me.
Even more impressive.
What kind of conversations
do you guys have
about football and the sort of dangers
of your chosen profession?
- Well obviously, he
understand as well as I do
that football is a dangerous sport.
I have two younger
brothers, Evidence Njoku,
he plays at Miami right
now, University of Miami.
And my youngest one, Charles
Njoku, he just arrived
at UCLA to start his summer
program as a receiver.
They both play receivers.
So, we all understand
that football is obviously
a dangerous sport, but at the
same time, it is our passion.
And we work extremely hard
to be the best we can be.
So my oldest brother,
Innocent, he understands that.
He loves our passion
for it, but obviously,
he's the one saying be
careful, make sure you're safe
and everything so yeah
that's pretty much it.
- I guess it can be handy to have somebody
like that in the family.
- Yeah, I always tell him
that once the three of us
are done playing football,
he has to take care of us
in all shapes and forms,
so yeah it's all love
at the end of the day.
- Well hopefully, he
doesn't have much to do
in that regard.
- David, thanks so much for
joining us and best of luck.
- My pleasure, thank you very much.
- So if you're Baker Mayfield,
the Browns quarterback,
you have Njoku, you
have Odell Beckham Jr.,
you have Jarvis Landry at receiver,
along with Nick Chubb and
Kareem Hunt in the backfield
when Hunt's suspension is over.
Those five combined for
41 touchdowns last year,
and they also had 641 touches.
So I guess the big question,
a good problem to have,
is there enough to go around in
that Cleveland Browns offense?
- A lot of pieces.
You know, there's a great
collection of talent,
but are they a team?
And that's what's gonna
fall on Freddie Kitchens,
because the Cleveland
Browns are in a position
they haven't been in in a long time
where they are the hunted.
And it's a totally
different position to be in
going forward in the season.
They're gonna be on
primetime a lot this year.
- [Dan] They are.
- [Damien] Let's see
what they can do with it.
- [Mike] The one thing we
didn't see on that graphic
was the lack of experience
with their head coach
Freddie Kitchens, and I believe one day
Freddie Kitchens will be a head coach.
But one year ago, guys,
he was a position coach.
It's like learning how to drive
a car going 90 miles an hour
in the left-hand lane.
And in the division,
you have John Harbaugh
and Mike Tomlin.
Since 2007, Mike Tomlin
has the second most wins
in the NFL, John Harbaugh
has the sixth most wins.
So, from a coaching standpoint,
Cleveland is a distant third
behind those two rivals.
And how Freddie Kitchens
can meld that group
will be interesting to watch.
- Interesting to watch,
what we have coming still
on NFL Live today.
We're going to have more on
the Ezekiel Elliott situation.
Cowboys running back
not suspended by the NFL
for his recent incident.
And because tomorrow is Independence Day,
we're going to talk about the great
independent NFL plays of all-time.
Stick around to see what that's all about.
(exciting music)
(serious music)
- What's up Marquise, this is Juice.
Listen, it's not about
hype, it's about heart.
It breaks through walls,
and outruns demons.
- [Announcer] Showtime.
- It outworks everybody.
When they see that, they
ain't gonna know what to do.
- [Announcer] Lights, camera, action.
- The Baltimore Ravens
select Marquise Brown.
- Bless 'em, my boy.
- Dad, how do you get a job?
- Well, first you search
for one and that's terrible.
Send off your resume and wait,
and then if you're lucky
you work a job you hate
until you die.
Goodnight, buddy.
- [Narrator] New for summer,
it's Bud Light Lemon Tea,
brewed with real lemon peels,
and aged on real tea leaves.
Yes, it's real, no you're not dreaming.
Hey, don't do that.
(funky music)
- [Narrator] In every
trip, there's room for more
than just the business you came for.
Whether that's keeping up
with what you always do,
or training for something
you've never done before.
That's room for possibility.
- Look, make a wish.
- I wish I had a Biggie Bag from Wendy's.
- I wish everyone loves
each other, and was al--
- That was a great wish, Jimmy.
- [Narrator] Get a Bacon Double Stack
with a quarter pound
of fresh beef, nuggets,
fries and a drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
♪ Summer nights keeping me up ♪
♪ I wanna waste time just looking up ♪
♪ Sky full of stars mind wandering far ♪
♪ Like we're 16 dreaming in the dark ♪
♪ Love the wind in my hair ♪
♪ As I drive my car ♪
♪ Makes me feel free ♪
- [Narrator] Now, get exceptional offers
at the Infiniti Plus Summer Sales Event.
- They made the original hot? (echos)
♪ Used to shake up my Hot Flamin'
and mix them with Doritos ♪
♪ Talking about far back
we go way way way back ♪
♪ I don't care about that ♪
♪ I ain't sharing my snacks ♪
The original, now it's hot.
- So I can buy from Enterprise Car Sales,
and you'll take any trade-in?
- That's right.
- Great.
There you go.
- Well, it does need to be a vehicle.
- But, I need this out of my house.
- [Narrator] With a fair transparent value
for every trade-in,
Enterprise makes it easy.
- [Narrator] Planning for retirement?
Quick, what's your most valuable asset?
No, not these, it's time.
Because time gives you more
opportunity for growth.
So don't waste another minute,
go to PersonalCapital.com
now for a retirement planner
that takes the guesswork
out of retirement.
A dashboard that shows you all
your accounts in one place.
Even your net worth, all in real time.
You'll get all these free
retirement and investing tools.
Plus wealth management options.
Join, at PersonalCapital.com
- [Narrator] Giancarlo bashed
out a record 61 dingers.
- [Announcer] Giancarlo
Stanton, what a show tonight.
- [Narrator] The Judge's
moonshots made us all rise.
- [Announcer] You don't see
this everyday, this is special.
- [Narrator] And Bryce took the crown
with some help from his dad.
- [Announcer] Bryce
Harper has won the 2018
Home Run Derby.
- [Narrator] Who will own the Derby?
The 2019 T-Mobile Home Run Derby,
Monday at eight on ESPN.
- UFC 239 is Saturday
in Las Vegas with two
of the greatest UFC champions
defending their titles.
Jon Bones Jones battles Tiago Santos,
and Amanda Nunes takes on Holly Holm
in the co-main events on Pay-per-view
starting at 10 Eastern, seven Pacific.
You want to order the main
card, go to ESPNPlus.com/PPV
and be sure to download the ESPN app
if you're watching on your mobile device.
Tonight at six, we got Sportscenter
after the Get Up NBA Free Agency Special
with Kevin Negandhi and Elle Duncan.
They will have the latest
on Kawhi Leonard's decision
plus aforementioned UFC
Light Heavyweight champion
Jon Bones Jones answers questions
ahead of UFC 239 on Saturday.
And American Coco Gauff,
highlights from her
second-round match at Wimbledon.
That's Sportscenter six Eastern on ESPN
and the ESPN app.
Once again recapping our
breaking news here on NFL Live.
Ezekiel Elliott, the Cowboys running back
will not be punished.
The league found that he did not violate
the personal conduct policy in an incident
involving a security guard
in Las Vegas recently.
The NFL interviewed
Ezekiel Elliott on Tuesday.
They also spoke with his
girlfriend who was there
at the time of the incident.
And have determined that he
will not face punishment.
Guys, we've had a lot of
conversation about this,
but one real quick sort of wrap up
on the upshot of Ezekiel Elliott today.
- You flirted with fire again, you know,
you've been fortunate.
Now it's just focus on
the upcoming season.
- And for the Dallas
Cowboys, this is a really
important day, let's get it wrapped up.
We put it behind us, it's before July 4th,
now we can get to training camp.
It's one less distraction to worry about.
And now they can focus on
the Philadelphia Eagles
and trying to win the NFC East this year.
- Mike, thanks for the
help with the segue.
Tomorrow is, in fact, July 4th,
and it's called Independence Day.
So before you fire up your grills,
or dig your feet too far into that sand,
we wanted to take you through some
of our favorite independent
plays in NFL history.
These are plays where one guy did it
all on his own or independently.
How about Pat McAfee and the Colts 2014
against the Texans.
The kickoff, there's no
coverage at midfield,
so he recovers it himself.
- [Damien] That's a smart play
right there by Pat McAfee.
- [Dan] 2009, Bills-Titans
in the Hall of Fame Game,
Titans Punter AJ Trapasso takes the snap,
but it's a fake punt and
Trapasso's just gonna
take it all the way.
- Got some wheels.
- [Mike] There is no
tackling in preseason.
- [Damien] No.
- [Dan] How much fun did he have there?
Number eight, 1997 Vikings-Panthers.
Vikings quarterback Brad
Johnson throws the pass
but it's batted back to
him and sure I'll take it.
He's gonna run it right in
for a touchdown on his own.
Denny Green liked it.
- [Mike] Brad Johnson very
underrated career at quarterback.
- Absolutely.
- No question.
Number seven, Marcus
Mariota, this is the 2017
Wild Card Game, Titans-Chiefs,
I was there for that one too.
Mariota scrambles,
throws, but gets knocked
right back to him by Darrell Revis,
and he'll go ahead and score it himself.
Big comeback that day for Tennessee.
Number six, 2017 49ers against the Bears,
the punt and Tarik Cohen corrals it,
takes it from the 40
and he's not just gonna
let himself get tackled here, right?
- [Damien] I mean, he's
outrunning the coverage.
- [Dan] He had a plan and he stuck to it,
and look at this, it's
gonna pay off for him.
- [Mike] I'll tell you,
him and Jakeem Grant
are two of the most dynamic
players in the open field.
They're fast, they're quick,
and they're hard to tackle.
- [Dan] Speaking of fast.
(excited chatter)
How about Mike Vick, 2002 Falcons-Vikings,
tied at 24 in overtime.
Vick, play action, gets outside,
and no one's gonna catch him,
come on are you kidding me?
- [Damien] This is like a
walk-off home run right here.
This was it, this was the signature play.
- [Dan] The overtime game.
This is my personal favorite guy.
Number four, 1991 Cowboys-Lions.
The one and only Barry
Sanders rushing up the side
and somehow gets out of this mess.
Oh, they're just not gonna catch him.
- [Mike] Boy, you're talking
about stopping on a dime.
- [Dan] That's ridiculous.
- [Damien] I take it those
pictures are not in HD.
- [Dan] No, definitely not.
Barry deserved it but it was too soon.
Deion Sanders, 1989 Falcons versus Rams.
He drops the punt but he recovers,
and he's gonna take it back.
This is his first punt return touchdown.
I do not know if he also played baseball
for the Atlanta Braves that night,
but I know he did at some point.
So, very versatile,
independent kind of player.
Deion Sanders, he's going all the way.
- [Damien] Oh, he's gonna
high-step it into the endzone.
Speed kills.
- On the independent plays.
Number two is a Super Bowl play.
Super Bowl XLIII, you remember
if you were a Steelers fan.
James Harrison against the Cardinals.
It's first and goal for the Cards.
Kurt Warner is intercepted
by James Harrison.
Yes, he's gonna, he's gonna
run it all the way back.
- [Mike] When he catches
the ball, you're like
there's no way he can score
on this, there's no way.
There's too many guys that should be able
to track him down.
- [Dan] Those Instagram workouts.
- [Damien] How do you let him tightrope
the sideline like that?
Man, that's awful.
- Just push him out.
- [Dan] Big guy, though,
kind of hard to push him out.
Plus you've got like offensive linemen
trying to run him down.
- Oh.
- Oh!
- [Damien] Dan, what was all that about?
- [Dan] 2011 NFC Wild Card
Game, Saints-Seahawks.
Good offensive line work
here, but Marshawn Lynch
did a lot of this on his own.
Runs up the middle breaks tackles
left and right, stiff arm.
Beastquake, Beast Mode.
That was what a 7-9 Seahawks team
beating a defending Super
Bowl Champion Saints team.
- Yep.
- His balance for his size was remarkable,
he has incredible feet.
- Crazy, so those are
the independent plays.