- We heard Adrian talk about
it, there's no interest.
When there's no interest,
guess what kind of deal's
available to you, the minimum exception.
So we might as well put all 30 teams in.
- Right, no, that's very interesting.
Well, we're gonna have to see.
We might know more by tonight, right?
Could know about Kawhi by tonight.
Could know about Boogie by tonight.
Come hang out with us,
7:00 eastern on ESPN.
Until then, watch your phones
cause it's free agency.
Lot's going on.
- Come on US team,
let's do it!
(hip hop theme music)
(intense music)
- [Wendi] Coming up on
this Tuesday edition
of NFL Live, JuJu Smith-Schuster joins us.
He'll talk about taking over
as Steelers top receiver
and what his relationship with
Antonio Brown looks like now.
We highlight some of the
NFL stars that are nominated
for ESPYS, including a
look back at Drew Brees's
record-breaking Monday
Night Football performance.
Plus, we hand out our
own award for the player
with the best highlights,
Patrick Mahomes, Saquon,
or Kyler in the running.
Who will be crowned your Highlight King?
Happy to have you with us on this
Tuesday afternoon, holiday week.
Wendi Nix, Dianna Russini,
Victor Cruz, and Mike Tannenbaum.
We will start with news
regarding Cowboys running back,
Ezekiel Elliott.
Zeke is once again headed to
the Commissioner's office.
The Dallas Cowboys running
back expected to meet
with the Commissioner, Roger
Goodell, today in New York City
regarding a May incident in Las Vegas.
The meeting comes after an incident
at a Las Vegas music festival in May,
in which Elliott had a
confrontation of sorts
with a security guard.
He was briefly detained, but
never arrested or charged
in the incident.
Nevertheless, the commissioner
wants to hear him out.
Hear what happened.
Dianna, what more can you tell us?
- Oh, at this point right now,
we don't know what exactly
is going on in that meeting.
But they are meeting in Manhattan
to discuss Zeke's behavior
in that Las Vegas incident.
Jerry Jones, of course, has
stood by his running back
saying that he doesn't see anything wrong
with what he saw on video tape.
Again, Zeke was in
those handcuffs and then
those handcuffs were
removed, he was not charged.
He could still face
punishment if Goodell decides
that he violated the League's
personal conduct policy.
That's what this meeting is to discuss.
But as of now, we are not
sure what the future holds
but those that I've spoken to
with the Cowboys organization
strongly feel confident that
Zeke will not face a suspension
because of this incident.
- Mike, as a GM, I know you have players
who have had face to face
meetings with the Commissioner,
who had hearings or due
diligence, if you will.
What's your take on the process?
- Despite how the Cowboys are feeling,
a suspension certainly is in play.
We have to remember under
the personal conduct policy,
a player can be suspended even though
there may not be criminal charges.
And the fact that Ezekiel
Elliott is meeting
in person with the
Commissioner signals to me
that a suspension, albeit
one game, two games,
could be in play here, and
he was sent to New York
for a reason.
So we'll see how it plays
out in the coming days.
But his prior behavior
will certainly be a factor
in their assessment.
- Well let's shift gears
to between the lines.
Victor, how important is the run game
to this current Dallas Cowboys team?
- It's huge, especially
Ezekiel Elliott, right?
He's been the focal point of that offense,
especially from the
running back perspective,
year in and year out.
Things he can do with
the ball in his hands,
whether out in space or just
handing him the football
behind that fantastic offensive line.
I mean, he is, in my opinion,
the heartbeat of that offense.
Obviously, Dak is the leader,
but Ezekiel is the one
that makes them go.
As he does well, then you've
got the play action pass
and everything complements
the attributes of Ezekiel Elliott.
So obviously, if he's there to miss
any significant amount of time,
the Cowboys will be looking
to replace those statistics
and those numbers that he
puts up week in and week out
in a different way.
- [Mike] Yeah, and Vic, you
just hit the nail on the head.
When you look at Dak
Prescott, his pass rating
goes from 97 to 122, play action compared
to traditional drop back.
So you could see the
importance of the running game.
Ezekiel Elliott and
obviously opposing defenses
are focusing in on
stopping Ezekiel Elliott.
That's a very impactful,
in terms of his impact
on Prescott's production
to go from 97 to 122,
that's a huge jump in terms of
his play action productivity.
- A huge jump, and we'll
talk about Dak's deal
and when it may get done,
but I'd be interested to see
how all of you feel like
this Dallas Cowboys team
stacks up in the division.
- I think they're right there at the top.
I think they're competing,
obviously them and Philadelphia,
right there neck and neck.
Gonna be battling it out
throughout the season.
But I think they've got all the tools.
When you look at them defensively,
from the defensive line all the way back
to the secondary, they're
loaded at each position.
And then offensively,
like we just talked about,
Dak Prescott, Ezekiel Elliott,
Amari Cooper, Randall Cobb,
Jason, I could go on for days with this.
But they have all the talent.
- [Mike] All the receivers.
- [Victor] Exactly, they
got all of the talent,
and not to mention--
- [Wendi] They have a new
offensive coordinator which--
- [Victor] Kellen Moore, obviously.
Which obviously comes from college
and doing those different things.
So he'll provide some creativity
that we probably haven't seen.
Some different type of
plays that we haven't seen,
necessarily, from the Dallas Cowboys.
- You're not going with the Eagles,
you're going with the Dallas Cowboys
to win that division?
- Yes, unfortunately, nobody
in New York kill me, please.
But I'm going with the Cowboys.
- That's right, don't, that was Victor.
When does Dak's deal get done?
Do we see that done before
the start of the season?
- I think that deal will get done
before the start of the season.
In fact, even just talking to people
in the Cowboys organization
about the timing of it,
it's funny cause just a few months ago,
the way it was being explained to me was,
it was gonna be a while,
it wasn't gonna get done.
And now it seems that, I'm not sure where
the pressure's coming from.
I don't know why they're
feeling the pressure,
but in terms of trying to get that done,
it seems that that's gonna
be a priority for Dallas.
- You know, the pressure really comes from
what Dak Prescott's draft
day disappointment was,
is now becoming the reality
of a free agent opportunity.
Because he was not a first round pick,
which was a disappointment.
But he's now in the final
year of his rookie contract.
So unlike guys like Jared
Goff and Carson Wentz,
who had the additional fifth year,
he could get to the
market and he may not be
a perfect player, I'm a
believer in Dak Prescott.
Not cause only, what he can
do from a passing standpoint,
but the plays he makes with his legs.
If he made it to the open market
the way Kirk Cousins
did a couple years ago,
hard to say what he could get.
And, I know people could say well,
he could certainly get franchised,
but I could tell you from
an organization standpoint,
when you use the franchise tag,
the last position you wanna
use it on is the quarterback.
Because when you have a franchise tag,
that means that the player
doesn't have to be there
for the off-season program,
doesn't have to be
there for training camp.
He could come in the
Tuesday before opening day,
sign the tag, get paid
for the whole season,
and it really puts the whole offense
and all those reps that you
don't have together, Vic.
So it's really a situation where
the sense of urgency, Dianna, in my mind,
it's coming from the fact that this player
is 16 games away from
becoming a free agent.
- And then that quarterback
also feels that pressure.
And they don't ever really
feel like they belong.
Do you remember with the Kirk Cousins
situation in Washington?
He was always out there proving
and proving and proving.
I remember talking to him about it.
You could tell it was wearing on him,
because it was like, the
Washington Redskins organization,
they were just looking to
date and date and date,
and he was looking for a ring.
He wanted to get married and
he wanted to feel that love.
And he never did.
For the Cowboys to put that on Dak,
that may not work out for them
if they wanna make that work.
- You know what he's married to, money.
A lot of money, I am not
crying for Kirk Cousins.
But it is a point well made.
All right, anyway, circling
back to where we started.
That is Zeke Elliott, the
Cowboys certainly hoping
that he will not miss any time.
A video shows Browns
running back Kareem Hunt
being questioned by
police after an apparent
incident Saturday night.
This was at a Cleveland bar.
The video published by TMZ Sports.
It shows Hunt speaking
with a number of officers.
He was not arrested, they
did not make a police report
regard the incident.
This, according to a
spokesperson to Cleveland.com.
Still to come on NFL Live,
Steelers star wide receiver,
Smith-Schuster, he of JuJu,
joins us from across the pond in London.
Find out what he's been up
to during the off-season.
And the story of high
school football coach
born with one of the rarest
conditions in the world.
- [Rob Mendez] There's
definitely doubters out there,
like parents, yeah, my
son is getting coached
at quarterback from a
guy that has no legs.
That lights a fire under my butt,
and probably gets me
excited to really just try
to prove people wrong about it.
- [Commentator] Double fault by Crawford
gives the title to Perry, six-three.
- [Announcer] Lift off, we have lift off.
- [Second Announcer] Saturated
colors now means Wimbledon
can be seen in all it's glory.
- [Commentator] Have gone back
to the champions of champions.
(Commentator speaking in foreign language)
- [Commentator] It's a Wimbledon moment.
- [Male Radio Announcer] Roger
Federer really is the glory.
- [Female Radio Announcer]
Mars rover has landed.
- [Commentator] It is sensational.
- [Second Commentator]
The waiting is over.
- [Third Commentator] And another golden
moment from Wimbledon.
- [Male Speaker] Hello?
- [Woman Speaker] Wendy here
from the New York Times.
(intense music)
(chattering)
- [Male Speaker] Hey, you see this?
(mouse clicking)
♪ Hello ♪
- [Male Speaker] Flaming hot nacho?
They made the original hot, hot, hot?
(hip hop music)
♪ Hello ♪
♪ Shake up my hot flamers
and mix 'em with Doritos ♪
♪ Why all the people in my face ♪
♪ Wanna be my ace, wanna be my amigo ♪
♪ Hello ♪
♪ Talkin' 'bout how far back we go ♪
♪ Way way back ♪
♪ I don't care about that ♪
♪ I aint sharin' my snacks ♪
- I made this for you.
- Wonderful.
♪ Hello ♪
- [Singer] Now it's hot.
- [Mother] Look, make a wish.
- I wish for a Biggie Bag from Wendy's.
- I wish everyone loved
each other, and was all--
- That was a great with, Jimmy.
- [Announcer] Get a bacon double stack
with a quarter pound of fresh beef,
nuggets, fries, and drink
for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
(upbeat music)
♪ Summer nights ♪
♪ Keepin' me up ♪
♪ I wanna waste time ♪
♪ Just looking up at the sky ♪
♪ Full of stars ♪
♪ Mind wanderin' far ♪
♪ Like we're 16 ♪
♪ Dreamin' in the dark ♪
♪ Love the wind in my hair ♪
♪ As I drive my car ♪
♪ It makes me feel free ♪
- [Ad Announcer] Now
get exceptional offers
at the Infiniti plus summer sales event.
(upbeat music)
- [Ad Announcer] In every
trip, there's room for more
than just the business you came for.
Whether that's taking in every moment,
or capturing the moment
worth bringing back.
That's room for possibility.
- So I can buy from Enterprise car sales
and you'll take any trade in?
- That's right.
- Great.
There you go.
- Well, it does need to be a vehicle.
- But I need this out of my house.
With fair, transparent
value for every trade-in.
Enterprise makes it easy.
(grill sizzling)
(jacket unzipping)
(festive song playing in foreign language)
- [Ad Announcer] Tecate,
bold on the outside.
Light on the inside.
(people chattering)
- Yes?
- We were all shocked that the
Odell-icatessen's first pick
of the fantasy draft would be a rookie.
Who shaped your strategy?
- [Male Interviewee] At this time--
- I'll take this one, Lindsey, his mom.
- Rollin' with Mahomies.
- I'm sorry, my lawyer says I
can't speak at this moment so.
- Honey Funches of Oats,
is there any connection
between your attire, and
your record last season?
- Oh, no.
- [Ad Announcer] Do you
take your fantasy draft
as seriously as we do?
Prove it for the chance to
have Commissioner Goodell
host your league's draft
live at NFL headquarters.
(intense music)
- [Show Announcer] NFL
Live is brought to you by
Nutro wholesome essentials pet foods.
Nutro, feed the clean.
And Geico.
15 minutes could save
you 15 percent or more
on car insurance.
- [Wendi] Press coverage now,
from our own Dan Graziano.
Sources according to Dan, CBA,
that's collective bargaining agreement,
talks between the NFL and
the player's association
are expected to intensify this summer
in an effort to get a new
deal done by the start
of the 2019 season.
Three to four negotiating
sessions possible
in the month of July alone.
Former Packers wide
receiver, Randall Cobb,
signed by the Cowboys in free agency,
teamed up with Aaron Rodgers for over
5,000 receiving yards after being drafted
by the Pack in 2011.
He will face his former
team week five in Dallas.
He had to say this about
moving on from Green Bay.
"It's like the ex-girlfriend
that broke up with you.
"When you see her five years
later, you hope you're in
"a better situation than you were before.
"Married, with kids,
and you're able to say,
"Yeah, I did better without you."
You know what, he's right.
No body says that, but
that's how everybody feels.
- Yeah, but not every breakup
has to be contentious.
- It doesn't matter.
I don't care if it's
the best breakup ever,
you don't wanna be like,
oh life wasn't so great.
- You're winning, I'm not.
- You wanna win, sorry,
it just is what it is.
OK, anyway, that got us
thinking five years from now,
who's better off?
OK, we saw a number of
NFL breakups, if you will.
So again, five year mark.
Randall Cobb or the Green Bay
Packers, who's better off?
- I'm going with Randall Cobb.
I think he's joining a team in the Cowboys
that's a younger team.
I think they're an overall
better team right now
than the Green Bay Packers.
But I think in five years,
he'll be in the playoffs
a couple times.
He's obviously in the mix
of that wide receiving core.
He's gonna be a focal point
in that slot position.
That's an important position
now a days in the NFL.
And I think overall, he'll just be better.
Dak Prescott, he's got
a younger quarterback.
I think that'll serve him better.
Obviously giving that longevity
and be there for a couple years.
He can built that comradery
and that continuity
with Dak, which will serve him
better five years from now.
- All right, he's not gonna
miss Aaron Rodgers at all, no.
- They're a better overall team.
- Again, five years, we
don't know, a lot can happen.
- They're younger.
- All right, listen, in my opinion,
no more notable breakup
than that one between
Odell Beckham Jr and the New York Giants.
This one's easy if you talk about now,
but we're talking about
five years from now.
Dianna, who's better off?
- I'm gonna go Odell
Beckham Jr is gonna be
in a much better position.
Well first of all, he got paid.
He got tons of money
and he has opportunity
to make more money.
Price of living in Cleveland
is lower, taxes are lower.
So from a personal financial standpoint,
Odell Beckham Jr is winning big time.
But when it comes to football,
there's no quarterback that
I believe has more potential
to be one of the greatest, than I believe,
in what Baker Mayfield could do.
In terms of the continuity and the team
that they're building in Cleveland,
compared to what they're
doing in New York.
We're not sure what's gonna
happen to Pat Shurmur,
if he's gonna be there.
You have to feel like he
could be on the hot seat
this year if it doesn't work.
It seems that Cleveland
is a much better off space
for Odell Beckham Jr, so I think
he's gonna look back and go
you know what, that was good.
- That was good.
What's interesting is the
Giants had a couple of breakups.
Also Landon Collins, who's
better off in five years?
- Yeah, I'm gonna go the
other way here, Dianna.
I'm gonna go with the New York Giants.
Dave Gettleman and that front office.
When we look at what they've already done
to replace Landon Collins.
They acquired Antoine
Bethea in free agency
and Jabrill Peppers, that
was part of the trade
that send Odell Beckham Jr--
- [Wendi] First rounder, yep.
- [Mike] To Cleveland.
And although Collins is a good player,
I thought he was more productive
closer to the line of scrimmage.
I think when you look at
the way Peppers plays,
he can replace him.
He's younger, more athletic,
and less expensive.
So Wendi, it's not five
years, we know right now.
We're better off without Landon.
- Wow, all right, fair enough, noted.
You know, I said there
was no bigger breakup.
As soon as I said that I thought
about AB and the Steelers.
I'm gonna retract that.
But anyway, Antonio
Brown and the Steelers.
This one, I think, is tricky.
'Cause again, we're five
seasons out, who's better off?
- I'm going with the Steelers here.
I really feel like the Steelers
organization as a whole,
they're gonna turn the page fully
from the Antonio Brown drama.
They're gonna be looking to
JuJu, he's gonna be tenured.
He's gonna be a true
veteran leader on that team.
Understand who he is.
Big Ben, who knows how
many years he has left,
but with that body frame, and
if he takes care of himself,
he can still be there five years from now
playing at a high level.
But these guys are ready to play.
I think as a team, as a perspective,
once they get rid of the drama
and get rid of the negativity
that was surrounding the
team with Le'Veon Bell
and all of these things, I
think five years from now,
this team will be better,
Ben Roethlisberger
will be relaxed, and the
team will be good to go.
- All right, perfect segue.
How about Le'Veon Bell and
the Pittsburgh Steelers?
- Well, I think we saw a
little bit of a sneak preview
last year, right?
Bell was a Steeler, but he really wasn't.
- Not really.
- So we're gonna go with
the Pittsburgh Steelers,
and obviously we're
talking about James Conner,
who filled in last year for Le'Veon Bell.
We have another year with him
now in the off-season program,
and I think really where
we're gonna miss Bell, guys,
isn't as a rusher, but as a receiver.
But James Conner is a
really good running back.
He's productive between the tackles,
he's a good pass protector,
and again, another year
of growing into the job,
I think Pittsburgh year in
and year out does a great
job of letting guys move on.
I think that replacing
Bell, I agree with Victor,
and I think, replace AB, I
think they're gonna replace Bell
very well with James Conner.
- I do think that team has sort of rallied
around these departures, that's now.
We'll see where they are in a few seasons.
This last one, I don't
even think you can count it
as a breakup, I'm not sure
they even really dated.
I don't know, they went out.
- It was a hook-up.
- It was a hook-up, Josh
Rosen and the Cardinals.
- I think Josh Rosen
is gonna be better off.
Look, this kid had the weight of the world
on his shoulders.
He was a top draft pick, he
was supposed to be the savior.
The answer to the Arizona
Cardinals organization.
Of course, that didn't work
out, so here he is in Miami now.
The pressure's really off.
He's got a new head coach here.
They're gonna be running
a New England system.
By the way, if you run the
New England offensive system,
you gotta be a smart guy.
That's what Josh Rosen is.
He's a smart guy, and I think
he's gonna fit in well there
and it's gonna be a place, by the way,
he also will have Fitzpatrick behind him,
who doesn't really seem
to have the attitude
of a starter that doesn't wanna help.
So you have two smart guys
in a quarterback room,
it seems like that's a much better place
for Josh Rosen to flourish.
- Dianna, what about Kyler Murray?
You don't think Arizona with Kyler Murray
has a chance to be a dynamic play maker
and five years from now, we're probably--
- That's really what
this question is right?
It's an assessment of Kyler
Murray in a lot of ways.
- No, it definitely is,
again, the big question mark,
of course, is is it gonna
work with Kliff Kingsbury.
But to me, my biggest issue with Arizona,
is last year and this year,
is their offensive line.
So as much as we can
say Kyler Murray can--
- I got five years to
fix it, in five years.
- That's right, he's looking
for a GM job right here.
- No, I'm not!
You trying to get rid of me?
We've got five years, I'm just--
- Breaking up is hard to do.
- You gave us five years, right?
- I gave you five years, I did.
- That's a lot of drafts.
- Fair enough.
All right when we come back,
JuJu smith-Schuster isn't
thinking five years,
he's thinking right now.
We'll talk role models and
Steelers culture coming up.
- Hi I'm JuJu Smith-Schuster,
and I'm gonna tell you
how much fun I'm having this off-season.
(intense music)
♪ Break break chains that hold me down ♪
♪ I make make waves all around ♪
♪ Still unstoppable ♪
♪ I'm still unstoppable ♪
(construction work sounding)
- Let me get this straight.
After a long day of hard work,
you have to do more work?
Everyday, you're nearly fried
to a crisp professionally.
Can someone turn on the AC?
No, oh, right, cause there isn't any.
Here.
- [Ad Announcer] Automatically
sort your expenses
and save over 40 hours a month.
- Without you we wouldn't
have electricity.
Our hobby would be going to bed early.
- [Ad Announcer] You earned it,
we're here to make sure you get it.
- It's time to get yours.
- [Ad Announcer] QuickBooks, backing you.
(dogs barking)
(soft music)
- [Male Character] What about him?
♪ I know ♪
- [Male Character] Let's do it.
♪ These winding roads ♪
♪ They lead me home ♪
♪ To you now go ♪
- [Female Character] C'mon.
- [Ad Announcer] This
summer, add a new member
to the family.
Hurry in to the Mercedes-Benz
summer event today
for exceptional offers.
Lease the GLC 300 SUV
for just $419 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz
summer event, going on now.
- This is our moment,
let's get it, three--
- Two, one, here we go, Peloton.
♪ It ain't my fault that
I'm out here getting loose ♪
- Let's do this together, Peloton.
- [Announcer] One subscription
for the whole family.
Just one part of the best cardio machine
on the planet, Peloton.
- Hi, Phil Swift here.
People everywhere tell
me how much they love
the Flex Seal family of products.
- This stuff is awesome.
- It really works.
- Best stuff I ever got.
- [Phil] Nothing compares to the strength
of original Flex Seal, Flex
Seal liquid, Flex Shot,
Flex Tape, and Flex Glue.
Now you can coat, patch, seal, and repair.
Imagine everything you can do
with the Flex Seal family of products.
Available at these fine retailers.
- Nice one, Mallory.
What's this?
- [Third Coach] Oh, it's
their new goal celebration.
- They're calling it the
Hulu has live sports.
You got your standard issue
couch, and there, a TV.
- How much is Hulu paying them for this?
- Hulu has live sports!
- Boom.
♪ Money ♪
(intense music)
- [Ad Announcer] Built by
champions and contenders.
Built towards the future on
the foundation of our past.
Built to defy expectations
and challenge convention.
Built by those who came
before and everyone to come.
Get your tickets today to
witness the 2019 US Open.
Built for glory.
(soft vocalizing to serene music)
(bell chiming)
- [Ad Announcer] Tales
returns, tonight at 9:00
- That one's nice.
Oh, I like that style.
- Car shopping?
- That obvious?
- Try CarGurus.
- [Dark haired Female] CarGurus?
- It's easy to find the cars you like
and compare deals.
Every car is rated from
great deal to over priced.
And the best deals are sorted first.
- CarGurus gives you dealer reviews, too.
- Look at that model.
Jinx.
- Jinx.
- [Announcer] Go to CarGurus
today to find great deals
from top rated dealers near you.
- Go long, pal.
(grunting)
(rock music)
- Is this where the immaculate
reception football is?
Was running out of bounds ever an option?
- No, no, no.
- Whenever I say we're gonna win the game,
I guarantee you, I meant it.
- Automobile 1920s, started the NFL.
Quit looking at my chest
hair look at the play.
- Get them white legs up!
(intense music)
- [Commentator] That
is JuJu Smith-Schuster.
Smith-Schuster past mid-field.
A leaping grab by the man called JuJu.
JuJu, JuJu Smith-Schuster
in the back of the end zone.
Wow!
(upbeat music)
- We're joined this afternoon
by JuJu Smith-Schuster,
who's making his way all
the way across the Atlantic.
He is in London this
afternoon for the NFL academy
where he's an ambassador.
JuJu, tell us exactly what that is
and what it means there in London.
- So here in London,
we're working with the NFL academy,
which is an amazing thing
because they give the opportunity
to some players, young players,
from the age 15 and up,
who learn the new game, American football.
This is new to them, which is awesome.
But it's awesome because
it just gives them
the opportunity that
they have another career,
another goal that they can
set to play in the states,
to play in the NFL.
- JuJu, we talked to
James Conner yesterday.
He talked about turning the page,
about the changes that
had gone on in Pittsburgh
during the off-season.
What's the temperature of this team
as you get ready for training camp?
- We're at a 70, we're not
too cold or we're not too hot.
So the weather's really nice right now.
In our locker room,
everyone's on the same page.
Focused on the same goal.
Which is amazing because
that's what we're all about.
We're all about the team,
there's no individuals.
And we're here to win games
and win championships.
- [Victor] JuJu, talk to
me about some of the talent
you're seeing out there
in London behind you.
Any ballers out there?
Any future Steelers out there or what?
- Oh man, there's some talent
out here, some potential.
You gotta understand,
this game is new to them.
We started lifting weights
at 14, these guys are barely
starting at 16 or 17.
So if we were to get
them on the right page,
onto the academy, it would be amazing
to start a Pop Warner team,
eventually start through
middle school, high school,
and that would be their academy.
- All right, JuJu, it's
been well documented
that Antonio Brown's no
longer with the Steelers.
Now you're the number one guy.
How's it feel, do you feel a
difference in the locker room?
Are people treating you differently?
Are dudes getting your
trays of lunch for you?
Is it a different feeling
being the number one guy?
How's it feel?
- Nah, man, there's no difference.
Obviously people say,
yo, you're the number one
guy this year, but more for myself,
I just see more opportunity,
not just for myself but
for other guys to step up.
You talk about AB having 100
catches, over 1000 yards.
Those yards, those catches
are gonna be spread out
between our offense, between
James Conner, Vance McDonald,
James Washington, Dante
Moncrief, a lot of guys.
James Samuels, there's so many guys
who are getting more touches,
more catches, more yards,
more YAC, just to help them individually.
But at the end of the day,
I'm still the same dude
in the locker room, same
JuJu, the same person.
I'm just, last year I was 21 and this year
I'm 22, same thing.
- [Victor] That's what's up.
- [Wendi] 22 year old version
of JuJu Smith-Schuster.
JuJu, you referenced the
football being spread around,
that makes the communication
with Ben Roethlisberger
all that more important.
What's your relationship
like with your quarterback?
- It's amazing, man.
Ben is a great leader, a great dude.
He took the whole offensive group
down to his lake house in Georgia.
Amazing, we spent time together
bonding, we worked hard,
we threw, but at the end of the day,
it's more so building that
bonding and that connection.
What he did for us was amazing.
I think it's so crazy that a
guy who's been in the league
for 15, 16 years, he sees
so many guys come and go
and for me, I'm only 22 years old.
When I met him I was 20 years old
and our bond is just gonna keep growing.
- I know as a superstar
athlete that you are,
you're always working on something new,
you're always working on something
new to perfect your game.
Gimme one thing you've been
working on this off-season
to just either get better at,
or something you wanna add
to your game or whatever the case may be.
- Man, I been really, really
focusing on playing more
inside and outside,
learning the whole package.
Learning the whole offense.
That's what separates being
on the field the whole game
and being on the field for
certain plays, certain packages.
I think it's great that I'm able to play
outside, inside, right side, left side.
Move me into slot, playing tight end.
That's gonna help out a lot.
That's something I've
really been focusing on.
It's studying that
playbook to the next level,
and understanding what
everybody has on the field.
- [Wendi] JuJu, we also get
to see everything else you do,
via social media.
Does anybody in the NFL
have more fun than you do?
- Uh, not necessarily, I do
a lot of stuff for YouTube,
there's a lot of stuff I do on that end.
I really love to show my personal side,
my fun side, what I do in my free time.
Playing Fortnite, do a lot of video games,
streaming, Twitch, and
making YouTube videos.
I think a lot of guys in the NFL,
they just post a lot
of working out videos.
Which, there's nothing
wrong with that, you know.
But what do they like to
do on their free time?
Do they like to travel the world?
Do they like to just stay
at home and watch movies?
I think a lot of their
fans would love to see that
and just get on a more personal base.
- Well, and some like
to go to prom, you know?
Which apparently you did recently.
Tell us about the prom.
- So the prom was awesome, a
kid, he's from PA, Pittsburgh.
Ideally he wanted to take this girl,
the girl that he liked a
lot, and his best friend
ends up taking her.
He told his best friend, too,
but his best friend kinda
went behind his back,
took his girl.
So he asked me and I'm just like man,
let's just one up this kid.
We buy a suit, we get a party bus.
We basically stole the night
away from him and his girl.
At the end of the day,
we all had a good time.
I met the guy, he seems like a good kid.
He's great, my friend's
great cause he got like
20K followers, Anthony.
So he's super excited about
his college career coming soon.
- Yeah, Anthony, one, friends
and girl friend, nothing.
He wins.
- Exactly.
JuJu, we saw you getting
busy on the dance floor,
we saw you getting busy on
the dance floor right there,
talk to me about what
celebrations you got in store.
I know you're always being creative,
you always bring some
new stuff to the table.
What you got in store for us this year
from the celebration standpoint?
- Man, look, I'm super excited.
Yes, I'm the young dude in
the room, but I'm very vocal.
It's my time to step up, to be a leader.
And what I mean by leader, I'm
getting everybody on the page
to do major celebration.
Like, Dante Moncrief, he's older than me
but he's gonna do these celebrations.
James Washington, all these
guys, all my receivers,
we're gonna do major celebrations.
James Washington's on the same page
because we're in the same class.
And then you know, I'm
still working on Big Ben
and the old lineman,
they're a lot older than me,
so they're vets, they've
been there before.
We'll see how it all figures out,
but major celebrations coming soon.
- We can't wait, last question.
We asked James Conner this
yesterday to close things out,
why should Steeler fans be optimistic
as we look toward 2019?
- Man, Steeler fans are
always there supporting
since day one, whether
we're doing good or bad.
I don't doubt that they'll
support us till the end.
I'm kinda happy with
where we're at right now,
we're not the headline.
The Browns, they're the team
that everyone's watching,
what kinda noise they're gonna make.
I'm super excited to watch them play, too.
See OBJ comment on my post,
and I'm commenting on his post.
Like yo, can't wait, who's
gonna have the best dance moves.
But like I said, this year,
the fans just support until the end,
because we're gonna finish strong.
You can always know the
Steelers pull through.
- [Wendi] All right, JuJu, best of luck.
We appreciate you being with us.
- [Victor] Thanks for being with us, Ju.
- Thank you, I appreciate it.
- With Antonio Brown
now departed to Oakland,
JuJu will become Big
Ben's number one option,
and with that he should
receive tighter coverage.
Over the last two seasons
when facing pressed coverage,
JuJu actually though
had a better catch rate
and yards per target than Antonio Brown.
Clearly,
Victor, perspective changes a little bit
I would think.
He's the number one guy,
he could say whatever.
What kinda pressure, how is it different
for JuJu starting this
season, than say, last year?
- I think the only thing
different is, like you said,
the mindset, the perspective.
Obviously you're coming
into that locker room
and Antonio Brown's not
there, it's just you.
And now, you become that leader.
People are looking to
you, you've been there.
You understand who you are.
I know you're just, what'd
he say, 22 years old,
but now you become the guy
that the younger teammates
are looking up to you wanting
to know what you're doing,
wanting to hang out with
you in the off-season.
Wanting to just steal a little
bit of knowledge from you,
your relationship with Ben.
They wanna get a head start
on what they need to do
to get better.
And he becomes the guy that
leads the charge in that regard.
It's pretty big shoes to fill.
- I think the Steelers
have done a great job.
I think they were preparing
for this for a number of years.
There is that whole notion
of, we have to win for today
and develop for tomorrow.
You look at that position
in that organization,
going back to Mike
Wallace, Santonio Holmes,
obviously Antonio Brown, Smith-Schuster.
They do a great job of
getting guys in the pipeline,
getting them developed.
And now Antonio Brown moves
on, Smith-Schuster steps up
to be the number one guy.
I think they've done
a remarkably great job
for a number of years,
especially at this position.
- I think that's a great point,
and I would argue that
outside of New England,
they probably do it as well as anybody,
in terms of continuity.
I know Antonio Brown ended in a way
they probably didn't anticipate,
but they did anticipate that
it would end at some point.
And to that end, Mike, and to your point,
they seem to be in lockstep
with planning for the future.
- I think there's three things
that JuJu Smith-Schuster
has to probably focus on this season.
It's going from being a great
receiver to an elite receiver.
He needs to play at that level.
Victor touched on the leadership aspect.
It's obvious Just from that interview,
you can hear he has stepped up
to already be that leader.
He's talking about trying to get
Big Ben and the offensive
line to participate
in the celebration drills.
They obviously have good chemistry there.
And then that third
layer is being a mentor
to those younger guys.
So he's gonna be asked a lot more of him
as a football player out on the field,
and then of course, in the locker room.
But if there's one thing,
I think, we've learned
about JuJu over the years
is he attacks everything
with open arms, he is
an open book himself.
He embraces that role, and he wants to be
that character guy, he
wants to be that good guy.
And when you talk to
players on the Steelers
about JuJu Smith and what
his personality is like,
because obviously on social
media he's so much fun
and he can be loud,
apparently he does a lot
of his work silently.
He's not the loudest guy in the room.
He's not the one joking
around during drills.
He likes to have fun, but
he's locked in and focused.
I think if he can take his
game to that elite level,
the Antonio Brown conversations
that we're gonna be having
are gonna feel so long ago.
- You know what else he said
that was really impressive
in the interview, he touched on at the end
about the Steelers are
always there in the end.
And it's not where you start in football,
it's where you end.
And you look at Pittsburgh
and New England,
those teams always improve
during the course of the season.
So James Conner,
Smith-Schuster in a new role,
it's not what they look like
in August and September,
are they ascending and getting better.
And Mike Tomlin deserves so much credit.
The player development, the
way they coach their players,
they get better.
And I thought his point
was a good one which is
hey, we'll be there in the end
because that's where they've
been year in and year out.
- It almost feels like they transform
and they kinda morph into
whatever they need to be to win
towards the second half of the season,
and that's what keeps them in
the hunt year in and year out.
- Well, and I understand,
for all kinds of reasons
why everybody's looking to Cleveland.
But I think you'd be unwise
to sleep on Pittsburgh
in any way, shape, or form.
Mike Tomlin as the head
coach, a veteran squad,
this is a good team.
I think that you could
argue, underachieved
last season, we'll see.
What do Patrick Mahomes, Saquon Barkley,
and Kyler Murray all have in common?
They make head turning,
highlight reel worthy plays.
We'll crown the Highlight King next.
- [Saquon] You ever watch
the highlights on YouTube?
- [Commentator] Patrick Mahomes on fire.
- [Second Commentator] Looks
one way, zings it another.
- [Third Commentator]
Barkley dives over the top!
Flips end over end, touchdown.
- [Fourth Commentator] Kyler
Murray, an absolute dime.
- [Fifth Commentator]
He's the best quarterback
you'll ever see at everything
else except height.
- [Sixth Commentator] Patrick
Mahomes with Mahomes magic.
How did he pull that off?
(upbeat music)
(serene music)
- I've waited my whole life for this.
(intense music)
- You ready?
- Are you?
(family hooting)
("Star Wars Main Title ")
- [Narrator] The ant
mindlessly marches on,
carrying up to 50 times its body weight.
It never questions the task at hand.
(car revving)
But this year, there's a more
thrilling path to follow.
(car revving)
- Kids!
Change of plans.
- [Narrator] Defy the laws of human nature
at the summer of Audi sales event.
Get exceptional offers now.
- [Announcer] Planning for retirement?
Quick, what's your most valuable asset?
No, not these.
It's time, because time gives you
more opportunity for growth.
So don't waste another minute.
Go to PersonalCapital.com
now for a retirement planner
that takes the guess
work out of retirement.
A dashboard that shows you all
your accounts in one place.
Even your net worth, all in real time.
You'll get all these free
retirement and investing tools,
plus wealth management options.
Join at PersonalCapital.com.
- I'm Tom from Kane 11 and
I have one question for you.
What size socks do you wear?
If you're like everyone else we've asked,
you simply don't know,
how could you?
All sock companies make their
socks in one size fits all
or just a couple of sizes
to fit every size foot.
At Kane 11, we make our socks
to fit 11 individual sizes.
From seven to 17.
That's right, 7 to 17.
No more heel hiking, toe bunching,
or that towel under your toe feeling.
Kane 11 has great colors and looks
to fit everyone's lifestyle.
From crews to athletics.
Even our perfectly designed no-shows.
Your feet hold up your whole body,
and the better your socks fit,
the more comfortable
you're gonna feel all day.
That's the Kane 11 promise.
So stop compromising your comfort.
Try a pair of Kane 11 socks.
You'll never go back to hit
or miss size ranges again.
See why Esquire, Men's
Health, and Golf Digest
are all raving about us.
Go to Kane11.com and get 20
percent off your first order,
only available at Kane11.com.
♪ Walk the world with me ♪
- Before we get down to slinging,
we like to set the mood.
- Dim the lights, put on
some musk, light a candle.
- And take a circ saw
to our old equipment.
(saw whirling)
- Ooh!
And let's leave the shades open
so the neighbors can see right in.
- Let 'em watch.
- [Announcer] Stop paying too much for TV.
For a limited time, get all
your favorite live TV channels.
Only 15 bucks for your
first month at Sling--
- Hiring was always a huge challenge.
Endless hours on job sites
with not a lot to show for it.
Then, I found Zip Recruiter.
They figured out hiring.
I post my job, they put
it all over the web,
and they send me the right people.
Because their technology is smart.
Zip Recruiter often
sends me the right person
in 24 hours.
- [Announcer] Zip Recruiter,
the smartest way to hire.
Try it for free at
ZipRecruiter.com/Direct.
- [Announcer] Whether you
need eyewear or contacts,
ordering from Eyeconic is easy.
That's because a lot goes into
making your experience perfect.
- I have an incoming order, sir.
- [Announcer] Your
order is double checked,
and saving money is easy.
- Prescription and insurance
verified, $220 saved.
- [Announcer] Choose from over 2300 styles
and more than 60 brands.
Get free shipping on all
glasses, sunglasses and contacts.
Plus, 10 percent off your first purchase.
Visit Eyeconic.com today.
(players chattering)
- [Draft Announcer] With the first pick,
the New Orleans Pelicans
select Zion Williamson.
The New York Knicks select RJ Barrett.
(crowd cheering)
- [Zion] You know, I
love the biggest stage.
I love the challenge.
- [RJ] My dream came true,
I'm just ready to work.
- [Wendi] NBA Summer
League action on Friday.
Triple header starting
at 7:30 eastern on ESPN.
You don't wanna miss a
special matchup at 9:30
featuring former Duke
teammates Zion and RJ Barrett,
facing off for the first
time in the Association.
Press Coverage now from
our own Josina Anderson.
An update, the NFL and NFL PA
have already scheduled
CBA negotiating sessions
for July 17th through the 19th.
It will be the first time
both sides engage in talks
for three consecutive days, specifically
on this pending league deal.
Dan Graziano also reporting there is hope
of getting a new CBA by the
start of the 2019 season.
- [Dianna] That's great news.
- [Wendi] Let's take a
look at a few NFL players
nominated for the ESPYS, shall we?
After an impressive sophomore season,
where he threw for over
5000 yards and 50 touchdowns
and won an MVP for just that.
Patrick Mahomes nominated
for best male athlete.
Saquon Barkley nominated for
the best breakthrough athlete.
Last season, Barkley burst onto the scene,
rushing for 1307 yards.
Broke a Giants rookie record.
Kyler Murray nominated
for best college athlete.
He became the seventh
player to win the Heisman
in OU's history.
None of those are too shabby, right?
But today we give out
the Highlight King award.
Is that an ESPY, it's not.
- It is not.
- It should be.
- But it should be.
- It definitely should be,
but it's funny because my choice here
is Kansas City quarterback
Patrick Mahomes.
He is up for male athlete of the year.
- But you're crowning
him the highlight king.
- He gets my vote, and here's why.
Against the Ravens, facing fourth and nine
from the Chiefs 40, Mahomes just did what
we had seen him do countless times,
which was buy time with his feet.
- [Mike] Get out of bounds.
- [Dianna] Relies on his right hand there,
finds Tyreek Hill down field.
And the best part is after
the game, Andy Reed said,
Oh yeah, that's exactly how we
designed it, yeah, sure Andy.
How about against the Broncos?
We knew his right hand was magical.
Did you just say lucky?
- [Mike] Lefty.
- Oh, I thought you
said lucky, I was like,
I don't think that was luck, Mike!
We knew his right hand was pretty magical
but his left hand here,
spots Von Miller coming right at him.
- [Mike] Semi-spiral on that.
- Even when your defense
is doing everything they should be doing,
there are situations where
you cannot beat Pat Mahomes
because he comes up with some
unthinkable moments here.
His athleticism, his vision of the field,
and his ability to stay in
the pocket and make plays.
And of course, outside
the pocket is where he's
perhaps probably the most dangerous.
Victor is here.
- I'm going with
Saquon Barkley, here.
- [Dianne] Oh wait, he's
your Highlight King.
Just to be clear.
- He is my highlight king, Saquon Barkley,
because he is a highlight machine.
As you can see, he's broken at
least 47 tackles on that one
to get to the end zone.
And this one, I mean,
he's just putting his foot
in the ground, he will not be
denied against Philadelphia.
Obviously a rivalry in that division,
and he's taking off on that one.
In this one, this one's pretty good.
OK, we know this guy's good.
First of all, tremendous
block by 73 right there,
but this run is just indicative
of the type of athlete
that Saquon Barkley is.
He can shake guys behind
him, in front of him,
he's got the speed to outrun
anybody in this league.
And that's what we see here
and it's always on display.
And then I get a bonus,
Dianna, I get a bonus one here.
Mike you'll like this
one, a nice little hurdle.
- [Dianna] Whoa!
- Plenty of running backs are doing that,
only a handful of guys, I
could probably count them all
on one hand, who can hurdle
guys in traffic like that
and keep it moving.
- Can you talk about that
mediocre protection, too?
He was able to jump.
Not to pile on your
Giants, but the fact that
he was able to do that with
that O-line is incredible.
- Got to do a lot on his own.
- All right, guys.
- [Wendi] Mike Tannenbaum.
- I got Kyler Murray, I was at this game.
His resiliency was unbelievable.
They got outplayed
badly in the first half.
He comes out in the second half.
He steps up in the pocket,
keeps his eyes down the field.
That puts so much pressure on a defense.
Throws a really accurate
pass, this was a great play.
Got Oklahoma back in the game.
This was another game I was at,
West Virginia's defense
was horrific in this game.
If they were playing flag football,
Kyler Murray still
would've gone untouched.
- [Victor] Looks like flag football.
- Yeah, I tell you what.
And this is what Arizona's hoping for.
Look at how many guys he
can make miss in space
and have the speed to take it all the way.
The amount of pressure
he'll put on defenses
will be formidable in the
fall because it'll be his arm,
and it'll be his feet.
Speaking of his arm, look at this one.
- [Victor] That was a dime.
- Oklahoma State, big rivalry game.
Again, 50 yards down the field,
hits Hollywood Brown in stride.
This guy is gonna be a dynamic play maker.
He is a highlight machine, he
is the highlight king maker,
and Arizona Cardinal fans,
that's what they're looking
forward to in the fall.
- They're hoping, fingers crossed.
Listen, we told you we'd let you vote.
We narrowed the field,
it's one of these three.
Highlight King, OK?
So go to our Twitter handle @espnnfl.
You can vote for one of these three
and we'll let you know what you think.
Also, by the way, while
you're at it don't forget
you can also vote on the ESPYS right now.
That is at ESPYS.com.
- [Victor] Get out of there,
Dianna, get out of there.
(group chattering over each other)
- [Wendi] Rob Mendez, a man
born without arms or legs
found his calling coaching
high school football.
- He comes out, full head of hair
parted down the side.
I told her, there's
nothing ugly about him.
He's still an angel.
(intense music)
(soft piano music)
- What's up, DK?
I know you're asking
yourself, am I worth the hype?
- [Commentator] Are you kidding me?
Why we love the combine.
- Can I live up to it all?
See that's the thing about hype.
(crowd cheering)
It could make you or break you.
Here's what I've learned.
They get to ask all the questions,
but only you get to answer.
- [Draft Announcer] The Seattle
Seahawks select DK Metcalf.
(crowd cheering)
- [Football Player] Good luck, DK.
- [Ad Announcer] Why use
Post-It Extreme Notes?
Because they make your message stick,
getting it said and done
right the first time.
- [Male Speaker] Oh, come on.
- [Ad Announcer] Stop the re-work
with Post-it Extreme notes.
(upbeat music)
♪ Summer nights ♪
♪ Keeping me up ♪
♪ I wanna waste time ♪
♪ Just looking at the sky ♪
♪ Full of stars ♪
♪ Mind wandering far ♪
♪ Like we're 16 ♪
♪ Dreaming in the dark ♪
♪ Love the wind in my hair ♪
♪ As I drive my car ♪
♪ It makes me feel free ♪
- [Ad Announcer] Now,
get exceptional offers
at the Infiniti plus summer sales event.
(upbeat music)
(vocalizing to electronic music)
- [Announcer] In every trip,
there's room for more than
just the business you came for.
♪ This wait is rolling let's get going ♪
♪ We got places to be ♪
♪ Oh oh ♪
- [Ad Announcer] Whether
that's taking in every moment
or capturing a moment worth bringing back.
That's room for possibility.
♪ Let's see how far we can go oh oh oh ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ Once upon a time I
was drinking Dos Equis ♪
♪ Now I'm just waitin' at the bar ♪
♪ There's nothing I can do ♪
♪ There's a really big crowd at the bar ♪
- [Ad Announcer] Summer
jams with Dos Equis.
Keep it interesante.
- [Ad Announcer] Exclusively
on ESPN plus, UFC 239.
She's the first woman in UFC history
to hold two title belts.
Now coming off a stunning victory,
rising star Amanda Nunez is set to defend
her bantamweight weight title.
Buy it on ESPNplus.com/PPV.
(dance music playing foreign language)
(commentator shouting in foreign language)
- [Commentator] Don't go anywhere!
(bell ringing)
- Your brother has paid
his debt to society.
♪ Brothers forever ♪
- I'm your girl, you're my man.
Him comin' home don't change a thing.
- [Male Boxer] I don't
need you bringing any heat
to my door.
I'm all the heat you need.
(soft piano music)
♪ And we'll be ♪
♪ Brothers forever ♪
- That one's nice.
- Car shopping?
- That obvious?
- Try CarGurus.
Every car is rated from
great deal to over priced.
The best deals are sorted first.
- Look at that model.
Jinx.
- Jinx.
- [Ad Announcer] CarGurus,
find your great deal today.
- [Ad Announcer] Hey,
guys, elcome to Hims.
- [Customer] Should have done it years ago
and I feel like the young stud
that I always imagined I was.
- [Second Customer] Outstanding product,
works above and beyond our expectations.
- [Ad Announcer] Go to forhims.com/ED
and get started for just five bucks.
- The ESPYS Auction is
where you can bid on
once in a life time
experiences like joining me
on the set of Sports Center.
That should be like a million dollars.
- Join me in Sunday Night
Baseball, in the booth!
- You can join me and we'll
make a puppet in your likeness.
- Come hang out with me
and my least favorite
son, Dan, on South Beach.
- [Scott Van Pelt] So
bid now at ebay.com/ESPN.
- The ESPYS Auction
includes amazing experiences
across sports and entertainment
including those you just heard about.
Go to ebay.com/espn to
bid, now through July 10th.
All proceeds benefit the V
Foundation for cancer research.
We've been highlighting
our ESPY nominees throughout the show,
but this one goes beyond football.
High school football coach Rob Mendez,
who will be the recipient
of the Jimmy V Award for Perseverance.
Born with an extremely
rare condition that affects
less than 100 people in the world,
Mendez found his calling coaching a sport
that he was never able to play himself.
SC Featured chronicles
Mendez's first season
as a head football coach,
capturing the inspiring and
unlikely story of a coach
who transformed a group of young athletes
from skeptics into believers.
(upbeat music)
(serene music)
(scribbling)
- [Cable] At this time,
I just want to introduce to
you somebody that I think
can really help turn this program around.
A coach that I hired
because I was impressed
with his knowledge of the game.
His passion as a coach blew me away.
(team chanting)
Everything else that's on top of that,
in terms of who he is and what he does
on a day to day basis inspires me.
Your new coach Rob Mendez.
(team clapping)
(string music)
(piano music)
- It was awful, it was
really, really awful.
I didn't have a choice to have an abortion
so I had to keep Robert.
- In the back of my mind, I'm
asking him why, why my son.
Less than 100 born like him in the world.
What am I gonna do with this boy?
- It was hard to see him, I
really didn't wanna see Robert.
So I didn't see little
Robert for about two weeks
because I just didn't know what to do.
- I just remember staring,
there was a lot of staring.
It would piss me off, really bad.
Like he was not a human or something.
- [Robert Sr.] But he was different.
- I'm under arrest, yeah!
- [Robert Sr.] He sees people
staring as an opportunity.
- Hey everyone out there, you
know it's me, Robert Mendez.
(electric piano playing)
- Things that you and I get to do
in 10 minutes might take him an hour.
But he never complained about it.
(piano music)
- [Josie] Robert was
just a really easy child.
- Again.
- And he just was really, really happy.
(group laughing)
- [Jackie] What's your favorite team?
- San Francisco 49ers.
- [Robert Sr.] He's got a
gift that doesn't require
him to be physical.
Making him aware of that,
I think he just took the ball and ran.
(inspirational music)
- I think the most difficult
part of having no arms
and no legs is simply not
being able to play sports.
I don't show it, I'm
good at not showing it.
But yeah, I get mad.
I get mad at God, I get
mad at the Lord, like why?
(calm music)
- His freshman year,
he was standing behind
the fence at a distance
watching them practice.
That was the beginning.
- We wanted to get him
involved in the program,
so we invited him to be our manager.
- They didn't know what I could do,
they obviously knew I couldn't play,
but just to include me, it
made me feel a part of it.
It made me feel, I guess
you can say, normal.
- He paid attention to us, as coaches,
but he learned the game
playing Madden football.
He created game plans on Madden,
and then he'd come to
practice and try to create
the same game plans and
execute them the same way.
- I started giving Robert a
little bit more responsibility
with my quarterbacks.
(whistle blowing)
- [Robert] Eyes on the quarterback, guys.
Eyes on the quarterback,
eyes on the quarterback,
- And the next thing you know,
he was there running the drills for us.
- Go, go, go, go, go.
Saddleball, when you roll
out, big eyes, big eyes, OK?
- His ability to study the game
and his ability to translate those things
to the kids is unmatched by
most of the coaches that I know.
- Right in front of the line,
right in front of the line.
Ram over, W orbit, 46 power.
- Let's go!
- Good job, good job!
Look it up, be ourselves.
I've been overlooked the
last three or four years
I've been ready for it.
When I go to a job interview,
sometimes I feel like I'm gonna,
scaring is not the right word,
surprise them.
And I don't know how they're
gonna take the surprise.
- As he rolls out, to be brutally honest,
when I first saw that, I'm
like, how can this guy coach?
And as he comes close, he goes,
gimme a fist pump, gimme a fist pump!
I just gave him a little
fist pump right there
on his shoulder.
And all that nerves that I
had was just melted away.
We had other applicants,
but I knew in my heart
that it would be a great fit
for these young athletes.
(soft piano music)
- I remember when Coach Cable hired me.
Cruising off the campus I was like, yes!
I just felt really accomplished.
Because it took me so long,
I knew I'd been ready for it
and I'd been overlooked,
and finally somebody gave me
the opportunity so I
really appreciated that.
- At this time, I just
wanna introduce to you
your new JV head coach, Rob Mendez.
(team clapping)
- Appreciate it, thanks Coach Cable.
Thank you, Coach.
You know, football is my passion.
This is gonna be my 13th year coaching.
I can't wait to get to know
every single one of you.
Believe in yourself,
believe in your teammates,
and believe in what you're doing.
Are we clear gentleman?
- Yes, sir.
- All right, I'm excited guys.
(team clapping)
(soft piano music)
- Obviously, it was a little shocking.
And there was jokes going around.
Typical teenagers, you know,
a guy with no arms or legs,
not a lot of people have seen that.
- If you're taken back,
that's just natural
and that's human.
But after the first two
seconds, it's just a normal guy.
- I don't care how good you are!
I don't care how experienced you are!
You guys are gonna do
everything as a team!
- Though he may not look like a coach,
he definitely acts like one.
- Lax nine, 157!
So what we're gonna teach
right now is called 31 zone.
- His knowledge of the game
for somebody who hasn't
actually gone through it is impressive.
On his phone, he could diagram a play
faster than I can do with pen and paper.
- There's definitely doubters
out there, like parents.
My God, my son is getting
coached at quarterback
from a guy that has no arms and no legs.
One, two, plant, good.
That lights a fire under my butt
and probably gets me excited
to really just try to
prove people wrong about it.
Perfect, perfect, good job!
- When they see him and
witness him and hear him,
I'd like to believe
that they take a moment
to evaluate themselves,
and anything that they've
gone through in life
can't be more difficult
than what he endures on a daily basis.
- One thing that I care
about more than anything
is being a family!
That is one thing I take
pride on, I love people!
I love you, I love you,
I love everyone!
So if you guys can't show
love on this football field,
then you better get off of it!
Towards you, Aiden, who am I gonna go to?
(grunting)
Whistle, whistle,
whistle, whistle, whistle.
If this was a game--
It was a fractured orbital bone,
and my cheek bone is fractured as well.
Couldn't sleep, I couldn't chew.
- I just felt bad for him.
You know, he's got a hard
life and I try to make it
as easy as I can.
(brushing teeth)
Things that you and I take for granted,
like brushing your teeth
or washing your face
or taking a shower or
going to the restroom.
(electric razor buzzing)
Robert needs someone to help him.
(soft piano music)
But he's tough.
Two days later he was at his practice.
- Hey Chuck, widen out,
widen out, widen out,
both of you!
- And his thing is, now, I
gotta be there for the kids.
- Go to the flat, go to
the flat, go to the flat.
- [Michael] He's been
waiting to be a head coach
for a long time.
- I didn't want to let them down.
I didn't want to let the kids down.
I just can't stay away, I guess.
Me being challenged
has been my motivation.
All I gotta say is who says I can't?
- [Team] Nobody!
- Who says I can't?
- Nobody!
- [Rob] Who says I can't?
- Who says I can't
originally came from me,
just having a drive to accomplish
whatever people doubted me for.
- Who says I can't?
- [Team] Nobody!
- Yeah!
(string music)
- If he's willing to do all of that,
then what are we willing to do?
(team chanting)
(crowd cheering)
- It's go time, we've been
working hard all summer long.
Prospect on three, one, two, three.
- Prospect!
- Go kick ass, let's go.
Let's go, run 638 stretch.
(cheering and shouting)
- [Announcer] Touchdown!
- That's how we do that,
that's how you do it.
Devon, let's go!
Those kids fought every single game.
I can't remember one
game that we were bigger
than the other team, but
dammit, we got the job done.
Oh, yeah, that's what I'm talking about!
That's what I'm talking about!
We got the momentum, keep it up, let's go!
(intense music)
- The JV team in the last 10 years
has had mostly losing seasons.
He just really has done a
job that I haven't been able
to see other coaches do
at that level before.
- I'm trying to send my
Y under, wherever it is,
over the middle, because
it's gonna be right here.
Over the middle.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Give me a hug, both of you
guys, good job you guys.
Appreciate it, all right, let's go.
- [Team] Who says I can't?
- [Rob] What?
- [Radio Announcer] Good
morning and hello, Prospect.
Ann Sobrato High.
Winner today wins the league.
- [Team] Seven, eight, nine.
- Remember this, I'm proud
of every single one of you!
But damn it, we're not done yet!
So let's go finish the job off right now!
(intense music)
- [Commentator] It might
take a miracle play
to score the only points in this contest.
Passes off to his right, intercepted.
4:37 to play in the fourth quarter.
Sobrato looking for the first points.
Kick on the way, has the
distance, and it's good!
(people cheering)
And Sobrato takes a three nothing lead.
- Let's just execute guys, right now.
OK, this is for the league
right here, OK you guys?
Rex Nine left, 180 smash, OK, let's do it.
- [Commentator] Fourth
and 14 for the Panthers.
Fourth down play, Jackson off to his left
and it's incomplete.
Sobrato gets the win and
takes the division title
with a win this afternoon over Prospect.
- OK, don't worry about it, man.
(player sobbing)
Come on, man.
Family is the most important
thing, remember that, OK?
That's what we built this
team off of, was family, OK?
We've got good days and bad days, man.
And today as a team, that's OK.
I'm very proud of the whole team.
It's gonna hurt today.
And that's OK if it hurts
because we cared a lot.
Because we love this game of football.
I really sincerely want
you guys to understand
how much I appreciate this.
You guys have given me
a lifetime of memories.
(forlorn music)
- Our opponents, they'd always doubt him
cause they see a man in a wheel chair.
To us, we see our coach, who's
perfect.
- When we're pushing him off the field
after games, it makes me feel
proud to have him as my coach.
- [Rob] Let's go with that flood play.
- These kids would follow
him no matter where he go.
You can actually see
the changes in the kids.
(shouting and cheering)
- Great game, can I give you a hug?
Can I get a hug, good game, brother.
- You want the best for your children,
and I told him one time,
you know, there's not a lot
of money in this, Robert.
And he told me, not everybody
does what they do for money.
He's right.
- It gave me the feeling of importance.
And I don't think they know
that and understand that.
Maybe they will one day but,
I love those kids and I'm
always gonna remember them.
Yeah.
I think we make a perfect team.
Can we agree on that?
- [Team] Yes, Coach!
- Can we agree on that?
- Who says I can't?
- [Team] Nobody!
- Yeah!
(team cheering)
- [Player] Way to go, Coach!
All right, guys.
- Well, several schools
in the Silicon Valley
recently notified Mendez of
varsity head coaching openings,
he's decided not to interview.
He says he has unfinished business
with his JV team at Prospect.
For more on Rob Mendez and
his remarkable journey,
head to ESPN plus for the
full half hour documentary
which you can stream right now.
And a reminder to catch
the ESPYS July 10th on ABC
to see Mendez receive the
Jimmy V Award for Perseverance.
With AB now on the Raiders,
what might JuJu's new
role be in Pittsburgh
as the lead wide receiver,
we'll take up that topic next.
- [Announcer] Keep up
with your favorite team
on the go with the NFL app.
Get all your updates,
scores, and live games
during the season.
Download the NFL app from your app store.
- That's the only circumstance
to which you would separate?
- Can't imagine doin' it any other way.
- [Kaitlyn] This is Kaitlyn Dickerson
from the New York Times.
This isn't the only case,
very little documentation.
(radio chattering)
I know that's not true.
And the shelters really don't
know what to do with them.
I just got another person
at EHS to confirm this.
I have this number, we're
gonna publish this story.
- [Announcer] This is a PayDay bar.
And there's only one thing
you need to know about it.
It has a truckload of peanuts
surrounding sweet caramel.
I mean holy
(drill whirling)
look at all those peanuts.
Best part is it helps
you get through your day.
PayDay, get to it.
♪ Nah nah nah nah ♪
♪ Hey hey hey ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
- [Announcer] The world's
first six function
multi-pro tailgate.
Available only on the next
generation GMC Sierra.
Get 20 percent below MSRP
on next generation 2019
GMC double cab and SLE crew cab models
with a standard tailgate.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Lower carbs.
Lower calories.
Higher expectations.
The light beer you've been
waiting for has arrived.
Corona Premier.
(soulful theme)
♪ La la la la la la la ♪
- [Announcer] Home.
(children playing)
It's so much more than a house.
It's your own little slice of heaven.
For over 30 years, Rocket
Mortgage has helped millions
of Americans finance the
home of their dreams.
- Toothbrush, honey please,
please just help me.
We've gotta go, guys, no!
- [Announcer] So you can spend your time
making your house home.
Rocket Mortgage.
Push button, get mortgage.
♪ I used to have to go in
to the auto parts store ♪
♪ Paid too much never found
quite what I'm lookin' for ♪
♪ Now I just go online
to Rock Auto and see ♪
♪ All the parts my car will ever need ♪
♪ Lower prices more parts more brands ♪
♪ It's so easy to find
the right parts fast ♪
♪ All the parts your car will ever need ♪
♪ Rock Auto ♪
♪ RockAuto.com ♪
- [Announcer] When you
need hot or cold therapy
for strained or injured muscles,
don't give up your freedom
to get your therapy.
Get that healing feeling with Copper Fit
mobile rapid relief wraps.
Hot or cold therapy
wraps that strap in place
and stay in place,
so you can do what you want
while getting the therapy you need.
- This is the best solution
for icing and heating
that I've ever found.
- [Announcer] Get that healing feeling
with Copper Fit rapid relief wraps.
Find the entire line of
Copper Fit rapid relief
mobile wraps now in Walmart Pharmacy.
- Hi, Phil Swift here.
People everywhere tell
me how much they love
the Flex Seal family of products.
- This stuff is awesome.
- It really works.
- Best stuff I ever got.
- I'm not sure what magic you guys do,
but this stuff is incredibly durable.
- We absolutely love Flex Seal.
I would recommend it to
anyone for any project.
It's fantastic.
- Imagine everything you
could do with the Flex Seal
family of products.
Available at these fine retailers.
(tropical theme)
- Bro.
- I got this.
- [Dave] Bro.
- Bro!
- Bros?
- Bro.
(elevator dinging)
- Bro!
♪ Bro ♪
- Bro.
- Oh, bro.
- Bro!
- Bro.
- Later, bromies.
- Bros?
- Bro!
- [Announcer] Stuber,
in theaters July 12th.
- [Wendi] UFC 239, Saturday in Las Vegas.
Two of the greatest UFC
champions defending their titles.
Jon Bones battles Thiago Santos
and Amanda Nunez takes on Holly Holm
in the co-main events on pay-per-view.
That's starting at 10 eastern.
Go to ESPNplus.com/PPV.
JuJu Smith-Schuster
will enter training camp
as the Pittsburgh Steelers
number one wide receiver
for the first time in his career.
Here is Smith-Schuster from earlier today
on what it's like, and the
expectations of stepping
into that role.
- I mean, obviously people say,
Yo, you're the number one guy this year.
But more for myself, man, I
just see it more opportunity,
not just for myself but
for other guys to step up.
You talk about AB having 100
catches, over 1000 yards.
Those yards, those catches
are gonna be spread out
between our offense.
Between James Conner, Vance
McDonald, James Washington,
Dante Moncrief, a lot
of guys, James Samuels.
There's so many guys who
are getting more touches,
more catches, more yards, more YAC,
just to help them individually.
At the end of the day,
I'm still the same dude
in the locker room, the
same JuJu, the same person.
I'm just, last year I was 21,
this year I'm 22, same thing.
- Yes, the older, wiser, more mature,
22 year old JuJu Smith-Schuster.
With a good YAC reference,
always a good day.
- Always.
- All right listen, this got us thinking,
obviously big shoes to fill
with Antonio Brown departed.
He's now an Oakland Raider.
So let's go one by one,
receptions, more or less.
Antonio or JuJu, Mike?
- Yeah, JuJu just made
all my points for me.
They're gonna spread the
ball around in Pittsburgh,
plus you have a head coach in Jon Gruden
who's the play caller.
They gave up a lot of
money and picks to get AB.
AB will have more receptions.
- I do think Jon Gruden
motivated to get Antonio
Brown the football.
How about touchdowns, Dianna?
- Touchdowns, I'm gonna
go with AB as well.
You know, you actually teed
me up perfectly there, Wendi,
because I think if there is
anyone that wants to make
Antonio Brown work in Oakland,
cause they have to figure out
why they pay him all that
money, it's gonna be Jon Gruden.
So he's obviously calling all
the shots on offense here,
and in terms of wide
receivers in the game,
we can debate all day
long who is the best,
but we all know how special AB can be.
As soon as he can figure
out that chemistry
with Derek Carr, I think he's gonna have
more touchdowns than JuJu.
- All right, there's
receptions, there's touchdowns,
and how about all purpose
yards, Victor Cruz?
- I'm gonna give JuJu some love here,
because clearly Mike and
Dianna have not given him
any love so far, but I'm going with yards.
He's the bonafide number one guy now,
which means in those pressure situations,
Ben will be looking to him to
be that number one receiver
and get him the ball in
space, either on drag routes,
deep routes, he can run
any route in the book.
And it's gonna be interesting to see
just how they use him
as the number one guy.
- Look, it's a team game
and all of those things
are what they are, but what
really matters, of course,
you hope anyway, are the number of wins
from each of these teams.
We've got the Steelers,
we've got the Raiders.
Who gets the edge here?
- Yeah, it's gonna be Pittsburgh.
I think we're gonna see an
improvement with Oakland,
especially on offense.
Josh Jacobs, Terrell Williams,
obviously AB, another year
with Derek Carr and Jon Gruden,
really worry about defense
and rushing the passer.
Obviously they lost
Khalil Mack a year ago.
While they drafted Clenin Ferrell
from Clemson in the first round,
it's gonna take a while
for him to get going
but I think they're gonna
be a work in progress
in terms of how they are on defense.
I'm going with Mike
Tomlin and a very mature
Pittsburgh Steeler organization.
- I think that's a pretty good bet.
How about celebrations,
is this even a question?
Well I guess, maybe.
- It's not a question at all.
I'm going with JuJu, mainly because
it doesn't even have to be him
that has to score to do the celebrations.
- [Wendi] He's made that clear!
- He's made that clear,
everybody's in on this thing.
So whether it's him or
whether it's Vance McDonald
or whether it's any other
person on that team.
They're gonna be celebrating
and JuJu will be leading the way.
- [Wendi] And let me tell
you, if you did not see it,
JuJu was with us about an hour ago
and he said that he is
working on Ben Roethlisberger
to get involved.
He has not committed, but he's trying.
- [Victor] We'll see him in there.
- We'll see about that.
- I like that you've become
the resident celebration expert for us.
It's like anything celebration,
we have to go to Victor.
- Here I am, taking a bow for you.
- We have one more
category, one more category.
How about we do the drama.
- Uh oh.
- Ah, the drama.
- Is it on there or no?
- Let's see here.
- I guess not.
- All right,
pretend.
- We'll just show the drama.
Speaking of drama, I'm gonna
go with what history says
and I think it's gonna be
Antonio Brown on this one.
Stick with that thought.
I like the way JuJu
Smith-Schuster is maturing
into not just a mentor
to these younger players,
but an actual leader on the Steelers team.
And for Antonio Brown, there are a lot
of personalities on this roster now.
Obviously we know Jon Gruden
is the focal point of this team
no matter who's on it,
but I think there's going
to be points during the season
where the AB of Pittsburgh
will show it's face in Oakland.
- You cannot tell, we will
not get through this season
without him getting irked with Derek Carr.
There's no way.
- It takes one sailed ball and he's gonna
come back like, really, really?
- Put some money on it.
The ESPYS are right around the corner.
Who is getting your vote
for the best record breaking performance?
Come on here, you know
Drew Brees wants your vote.
(intense music)
- [Commentator] Drew Brees has done it.
NFL's all time leading passer.
- You can accomplish anything in life
if you're willing to work for it, right?
(intense music)
- Remember that degree
you got in taxation?
Of course you don't, because you didn't.
Your job isn't understanding tax code,
it's understanding why that
will get him a body like that.
Move!
That.
Your job isn't doing hard work, here.
It's making her do hard work,
and getting paid for it.
- [Announcer] Snap and sort your expenses
to save over $4600 at tax time.
- Jodi, it's time to get yours.
- [Announcer] QuickBooks, backing you.
(doorbell ringing)
- [Woman] It's open!
- Hi, this is amazing.
- [Narrator] With moderate
to severe ulcerative colitis.
- Are you OK?
- [Narrator] Even when I was there,
I never knew when my
symptoms would keep us apart.
So I talked to my doctor about Humira.
I learned Humira can help
get, and keep UC under control
when other medications
haven't worked well enough.
And it helps people
achieve control that lasts,
so you could experience
few or no symptoms.
- [Ad Announcer] Humira
can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal,
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have happened.
As have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems.
Serious allergic reactions and new
or worsening heart failure.
Before treatment, get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB, Hepatitis
B, are prone to infections,
or have flu-like symptoms or sores,
don't start Humira if
you have an infection.
- [Narrator] Be there for you and them.
Ask your gastroenterologist about Humira.
With Humira, control is possible.
- [Announcer] How do you
gauge the greatness of an SUV?
Is it to carry cargo,
or to carry on a legacy?
Can show it's strength, or
it's sign of intelligence.
In crossing harsh terrain
or breaking new ground.
This is the time to get
an exceptional offer
on the Mercedes of your mid-summer dreams
at the Mercedes-Benz
summer event, going on now.
Lease the GLA 250 SUV
for just $329 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz summer event.
Mercedes-Benz, the best or nothing.
- [Announcer] Why are pet
lovers shopping online
at chewy.com?
- I really wanted another dog.
He was worried about the money.
- Yes.
- [Female Customer] With
Chewy, we save money
on food and toys.
- So finally I broke down.
- [Female Customer] And we
were able to rescue Max.
- [Announcer] Save 30
percent on your first order
today at Chewy.com.
- [Announcer] Switch to Metro
and get the best deal in wireless.
Get two unlimited lines for just 80 bucks
with Amazon Prime included.
- Fantastic!
- [Announcer] Plus, get two
free Samsung Galaxy phones.
Only at Metro.
- What's up, Kyler, it's Dak.
- [Announcer] The 135th
pick, Dak Prescott.
- [Dak] Trust me, I know
what it's like to be doubted.
- [Commentator] He's entirely too small.
He shouldn't even play quarterback.
- [Dak] Remember, though, doubt is a gift.
(cheering)
It takes you to the next level.
- [Commentator] Kyler
Murray is the best player
in college football.
- [Dak] So what if they doubt you?
- [Draft Announcer] The Arizona Cardinals
select Kyler Murray.
- They doubted me, too.
Go get 'em, bro.
(glass shattering)
- Nice going, Spencer.
- I can't believe we broke
old man Hennessy's window.
- Correction, dude, you broke it.
I just threw the ball.
- This is really bad,
what are we gonna do?
- We?
- [Boy] Go to the door
and ask for the ball back.
- Are you serious?
- It's my ball, Murtlebeck.
- I'm so dead.
- I'd run away.
- Yeah, to Uruguay.
- Kiss your life goodbye, sorry.
Let's go.
- [Boy] See you, add me to your will.
- [Boy With Bat] Some friends you are!
(soft music)
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Keep smiling ♪
♪ Keep shining ♪
- Hi.
- Tell him it was an accident
and we can fix the window.
Come on, I'll come with you.
- [Announcer] Loyalty, pass it on.
- You go first.
- [Announcer] A message
from The Foundation
for a Better Life.
- [Wendi] Next.
- [Commentator] Drew Brees finds himself
only 35 yards away.
- [Drew] It's about us, it's
about our strength, on one!
- [Commentator] Just Peyton
Manning left to pass.
- Blue 80, set.
- [Commentator] He starts
in shotgun, drops back.
Looks to the far side, wide open!
(crowd cheering)
and Smith, what a way to do it.
- I love you, bro, I love you, bro.
- [Commentator] Drew Brees is the NFL's
all time leading passer.
- Hey boys, how about that, huh?
- [Commentator] There's only
one word that comes to mind.
Greatness.
(hip hop music)
- Well, we continue to
highlight some of the stars
around the NFL that earned
ESPY nominations this year.
The amazing moment from Drew
Brees is up for the ESPY
for best record breaking performance.
Brees broke the NFL passing record
when he passed Peyton
Manning's mark of 71,940 yards.
Victor, you made this point
yesterday, and it's true.
I think last year was his
best bet at winning the MVP.
He just had this pesky
little Patrick Mahomes
who did things that just
didn't seem possible
to keep Brees from winning that award.
- Exactly, and then how do you amass such
a monumental record like this
on an illustrious career that he's had
and not win the league MVP one time?
I mean, obviously Peyton
Manning won a couple of those,
Tom Brady, all those tremendous players.
But he's gotta get it one time.
He's putting numbers
up each and every year.
I think there's years
that he kinda just goes
under the radar out there in New Orleans
with those play makers
and everybody he's got.
I think this is the year where he's like,
you know, we'll put a
nice pretty little red bow
on this career and put an
NFL league MVP under my belt
and get back to the big dance, hopefully
and keep things going.
- So in fairness, he has
been a Superbowl MVP.
Two time offensive player of the year.
But the Hall of Fame quality quarterback
that Drew Brees is, you
would like to see him go.
Although, I know he'd take
another Lombardi trophy
any day of the week.
- Now that, you can't dispute.
But at least give him one league MVP.
He's earned it.
- We'll show you why, how about this.
How about the best of
the best of Drew Brees.
- [Victor] This is vintage, right here.
- [Wendi] Yeah, vintage,
'04, he was at Georgia.
Play action, deep to Eric Parker,
breaks a tackle for a 79 yard touch down.
- [Victor] I like it, showing
that arm off real early.
- [Wendi] Black and white there.
- [Victor] Real pixelated,
grainy, I love it.
- [Mike] Pixelated?
- [Wendi] There you go,
2014 against the Packers.
Brees steps up, just lays this
one perfectly into the arms
of Brandon Cooks.
A 50 yard touchdown strike.
- [Victor] What a dime.
- [Mike] You know what else is great?
- [Wendi] That is a dime.
- [Mike] He's stepping up in the pocket.
A lot of times you see
younger quarterbacks
step up in the pocket
and just check it down.
He's stepping up in the
pocket and keeping his eyes
down the field, puts so
much pressure on a defense.
- [Victor] Teach tape.
- [Wendi] '06 against the Bengals.
The handoff here, it's a flea flicker.
- [Victor] Love it.
- [Wendi] And then Joe Horn there,
between two defenders,
a 72 yard touchdown.
And it's that kinda arm that we see.
And that's Victor Cruz-esque right there.
- [Victor] I like it, Joey.
- [Wendi] Moving now to the modern day--
- [Victor] I miss the cellphone Joey.
- [Wendi] Against the Panthers.
Brees here to Ted Ginn in the end zone.
49 yards right there.
- [Victor] The consistency
that we're seeing here
is with, he's not even being touched.
There's barely even people around him
while he's making these throws.
That's indicative to the type
of team he's been around,
that offensive line
taking good care of him.
- [Wendi] '06 NFC
championship, Saints and Bears.
Brees here to Reggie Bush.
- [Mike] That's a great example of
a really effective quarterback play.
Sometimes you have to throw
it as hard as you can.
That was a great touch throw.
He led the running back,
who takes it all the way,
but what touch he has.
And that's such an underrated
aspect of playing quarterback.
- [Wendi] Then 2016 against the Raiders.
The longest career pass, is this a 98?
- [Victor] Yep.
- [Wendi] Oh, he's got the--
I'm sure he wishes he was one yard back.
- [Wendi] Well he's got a
little yards after catch here.
To Brandin Cooks, an incredible career.
Certainly I think the Hall of Fame.
- [Victor] Gotta miss him on that one.
- And perhaps a future NFL MVP.
You can vote on the ESPYS
right now at ESPYS.com.
Again, Brees up for record
breaking performance
along with three other moments
including Klay Thompson's record
for three pointers in a game with 14.
All right, we gave you our opinion,
but who are you crowning
the NFL Highlight King?
Is it Mahomes, Saquon, Kyler?
Dennis Green let's us know
what's happening next.
- Now, if you wanna crown
'em, you crown their
(beeping)
but they are who we thought they were.
(intense music)
- What's up, Marquise, this is Juice.
Listen, it's not about height.
It's about heart.
It breaks through walls
and outruns demons.
(crowd cheering)
- [Commentator] Show time!
- It outworks everybody.
When they see that,
they ain't gonna know what to do with you.
- [Commentator] Lights, camera, action.
- [Announcer] The Baltimore
Ravens select Marquise Brown.
- Bless 'em, my boy.
(intense music)
- [Mother] Look, make a wish.
- I wish for a Biggie Bag from Wendy's.
- I wish everyone loved
each other, and was all--
- That was a great wish, Jimmy.
- [Announcer] Get a bacon double stack
with a quarter pound of fresh beef,
nuggets, fries, and a
drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bad is
everything you could wish for.
(ocean waves sounding
with seagulls flying)
(soda fizzing)
(exhaling)
(horse neighing)
(soda fizzes)
(exhaling)
- Yow!
(upbeat music)
♪ Summer nights ♪
♪ Keepin' me up ♪
♪ I wanna waste time ♪
♪ Just lookin' at the sky ♪
♪ Full of stars mind wanderin' far ♪
♪ Like we're 16 ♪
♪ Dreamin' in the dark ♪
♪ Love the wind in my hair ♪
♪ As I drive my car ♪
♪ It makes me feel free ♪
- [Announcer] Now, get exceptional offers
at the Infiniti plus summer sales event.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] In every trip
there's room for more than
just the business you came for.
Whether that's keeping up
with what you always do,
or training for something
you've never done before.
That's room for possibility.
(upbeat music)
- So I can buy from Enterprise car sales,
and you'll take any trade in?
- That's right.
- Great.
There you go!
- Well, it does need to be a vehicle.
- But I need this out of my house.
With fair transparent
value for every trade in,
Enterprise makes it easy.
(grill sizzling)
(jacket unzipping)
(festive song playing in foreign language)
- [Announcer] Tecate, bold on the outside.
Light on the inside.
- Before we get down to slinging,
we like to set the mood.
- Dim the lights, put on some musk.
- And take a circ saw
to our old equipment.
(saw buzzing)
- [Announcer] Get live TV.
Only 15 bucks for your
first month at slingtv.com.
- [Mother] Look, make a wish.
- I wish for a Biggie Bag from Wendy's.
- I wish everyone loved
each other and was all--
- That was a great wish, Jimmy.
- [Announcer] Get a bacon double stack
with a quarter pound of fresh beef,
nuggets, fries, and a
drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
- [Commentator] Double fault by Crawford
gives the title to Perry, six-three.
- [Announcer] Lift off, we have lift off.
- [Female Radio Voice] Saturated
colors now means Wimbledon
can be seen in all it's glory.
- [Commentator] Have gone back
to the champions of champions.
(Commentator speaking in foreign language)
- [Commentator] It's a Wimbledon moment.
- [Male Radio Announcer] Roger
Federer really is the glory.
- [Female Radio Announcer]
Mars rover has landed.
- [Commentator] It is sensational.
- [Second Commentator]
The waiting is over.
- [Third Commentator] And another golden
moment from Wimbledon.
(soft piano music)
- [Announcer] NFL Live is
brought to you by Geico.
15 minutes could save you
15 percent or more on car insurance.
(panel laughing)
- [Victor] I'm all about it.
- [Wendi] Canadian football league action,
Thursday on ESPN.
It's the three and oh Hamilton Tiger-Cats
taking on the Montreal
Alouetttes at 7:30 eastern.
To get ESPN plus, download the ESPN app
or visit us at ESPNplus.com.
Do not forget Sports
Center at 6:00 eastern
after the Get Up NBA free agency special
with Kevin Negandhi and Michael Eaves.
They'll have the latest on
Kawhi's deciding factors.
Plus, reaction and
analysis from the US Women,
their semi-final against England.
And of course day two at Wimbledon.
Sports Center 6:00 eastern on ESPN
and the ESPN app.
Everybody stated their case.
It's not a real ESPY, but
we're handing one out.
The NFL Highlight King,
and Dianna Russini who made
the case for Patrick Mahomes.
I don't know guys, I happen to agree.
- [Victor] It's the quarterbacks, man.
- [Wendi] The man is a highlight machine.
- I'm throwing a challenge flag here.
I wanna challenge flag here.
We're talking about the NFL, right?
We haven't had any NFL
plays yet for Kyler.
So we're in the wrong category,
we got the right player
maybe in the wrong category.
- So you were saying you were
handicapped from the get go?
- It was tough.
- OK, no crying in the big leagues, Mike.
- So put the pressure on you, then.
So are you going with team
Victor with Saquon Barkley,
or team Dianna Russini
with Patrick Mahomes?
- I'm a free agent, I'm going
with the highest bidder.
- OK, we'll see how it works.
- We'll talk off screen.
- Listen, July 4th holiday.
We wanna say a special thank you
to all our men and women
serving around the world.
We appreciate you.