(audience cheering)
- (sighs) um,
to be standing here representing um,
one of the greatest artists of
our time, James Baldwin, is--
(audience applauding)
It's a little surreal.
James Baldwin birthed this
baby and Barry (crying)
you nurtured her, you
surrounded her with so much love
and support so it's appropriate
for me to be standing here
cause I'm an example of what it looks like
when support and love
is poured into someone.
(sighs) Mom,
I love you so much.
(applauding)
Thank you for teaching me
that god is always leaning,
always has been leaning in my direction.
Gamosis, they'll ask me
about that later. (laughing)
So many people to thank, Chelsea Barnard,
who brought this project to Anna Perna,
Megan Ellinson, Anna Perna,
plan B, this amazing cast.
My sisters in art,
Marina, Amy, Emma, Rachel,
it has been an honor to have my name
be just said with yours
this whole step of the way
has been pretty amazing.
The Rivers family, Kiki,
Coleman, Tiana, Stephan. (sighs)
God is good all the time.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Please welcome Jason Mamoa
and Academy Award winning
actress, Helen Miran.
(gentle orchestral music)
(applauding)
- Well you know, honestly, I swear to god
that Jason and I didn't
coordinate our outfits tonight.
This was purely accidental, but you know,
it just goes to show,
doesn't it, that these days,
a Hawaiian god and a
very mature English woman
can actually wear the same color.
We can both wear pink. (laughing)
- Finally, times are changing.
- [Helen] Yeah.
- Boom.
(laughing)
- Documentary film makers bring us stories
of real people doing real
things and in doing so,
they can often open our eyes
to the most important issues
of yesterday, today and tomorrow.
- They're insightful,
they're illuminating,
sometimes astonishing, always
authentic and revelatory.
Here are the nominees for
best documentary feature.
Free Solo, Elizabeth Chai
Vasarhelyi, Jimmy Chin,
Evan Hayes and Shannon Dill.
- The chance of me
falling off is quite low
even though the consequence
is extremely high
and that's kind of like one of
the appeals of free soloing.
- [Helen] Hale County This
Morning, This Evening,
Ramell Ross, Joslyn Barnes and Su Kim.
- I don't want my son to
know that I didn't graduate.
I just want to make life better for him.
- [Helen] Minding the Gap,
Bing Liu and Diane Quon.
- [Man] I'm making this film because I was
physically disciplined by my step-father
and it didn't make sense to me
and I saw myself in your own story.
- [Helen] Of Fathers
and Sons, Talal Derki,
Ansgar Frerich, Eva Kemme
and Tobias N. Seibert.
(speaking a foreign language)
- [Helen] RBG, Betsy West and Julie Cohen.
- I ask no favor for my sex.
All I ask of our brethren is that they
take their feet off our necks.
(applauding)
- And the Oscar goes to,
Free Solo.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar nomination
for Elizabeth Chai Vasarhelyi, Jimmy Chin,
Evan Hayes, and Shannon Dill.
(gentle orchestral music)
(applauding)
(cheering)
- [Man] Wow, wow.
- Breath. (chuckles)
- Wow, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you National Geographic
for believing in us
and for hiring women and people of color
cause we only help make the films better.
Thank you to all the amazing
people who worked on this film,
Evan, Shannon--
- Our high angle team.
- I mean, it was a work of an army
and we appreciate you in every way.
Thank you to our families,
especially our two kids,
Brean, I know you're here.
- James.
(laughing)
- And then thank you to Sani McCannles,
you climbed your own mountain
that day, so thank you, Sani.
(applauding)
This film would be so boring without you,
I'm just saying, okay.
Okay anyway, thank you Alex
Honeld for giving us courage
and teaching us how to
believe in the impossible
and inspiring us.
This film is for everyone who
believes in the impossible.
- Thank you.
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Coming up, a look at Vice
and the awards for makeup and hair styling
and costume design.
And later, Melissa McCarthy, Tyler Perry,
Amelia Clark and a performance
by Jennifer Hudson.
The Oscars, on ABC, brought to you by,
the uncompromising Cadillac SUV's.
(birds chirping)
(chimes ringing)
(engine humming)
(cheering)
(mellow rock music)
(applauding)
(alarm beeps)
(engine starts)
(mellow rock music)
♪ Oh my god ♪
- [Woman] May the road
rise up to meet you.
May the wind be at your back.
Rise above with the
uncompromising Cadillac SUV's.
- I go to a lot of
different music festivals,
a lot of different
concerts and when I'm in
these large crowds, even when
I'm with tens of thousands
of people and I just love
being the friend with service.
It's really cool to be
able to take a photo,
take a video, be immediately able to
post it on my social media.
Because I am tall,
I get that good kind of
view on the stage, amazing.
- [Man] There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best
network now always includes
Apple Music on us, starting
at only $40, only on Verizon.
- [Man] To you, a filmmaker
of a future generation,
you and I, we're already
speaking to each other
from across time and I thought I'd share
this thought with you, if
you're burning to tell a story,
if you see the images in your
mind, then go make your movie.
- [Man] Your film will speak to many
with a singular voice.
Ask yourself what you have to say
and then say it in ways
that are unique to you.
(speaking Spanish)
- [Woman] Use your gifts to reach beyond
your wildest imagination.
Say what you believe.
Your voice matters.
(speaking Spanish)
- [Man] Pick up a camera and get going.
- [Woman] Take action.
I ask, if not you, who?
- And I'm looking forward to
hearing back from you soon.
Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- [Woman] Catherine.
- [Man] Marty.
- [Man] Jim.
- [Man] Alejandro.
- Open the pod bay doors, Hal.
Hello, Hal, do you read me?
Hey Google, open the pod bay doors.
♪ Aye, oh, let's go. ♪
♪ Aye, oh ♪
- [Man] Show me photos from last night.
- [Siri] Showing your photos.
- [Man] Oh no, no, no, no, no, no.
- You should just go to city college.
You know, with your work ethic,
just go to city college and then to jail
and then back to city college
and learn to pull yourself off--
- [Woman] Your lift has arrived.
(screaming)
(phone rings)
- Hello?
- [Man] Hello, are you ready?
- Yes.
- [Man] What door am I at?
- Patio door, police are on their way.
See ya.
- Show me the money.
- [Siri] Here you go.
(screaming)
(laughing)
♪ Aye oh, let's go ♪
- Hey Google, what's on my calendar today?
- [Siri] At 5:30 p.m., you have
appear in Google commercial.
- (laughing) That's never
gonna happen, mm mm.
♪ Let's go. ♪
- [Woman] You vowed to love this woman
for richer, for poorer,
for your cover story.
(grunts)
(thumps)
- I love it.
- [Woman] L'Espionnage
Jewelers, a stunning collection.
♪ Our harpies, boom, boom, boom ♪
- If we want this thing to work,
we're gonna need to connect.
- I don't do emotional attachments.
- I hate to tell you, you have the heart
and a capacity to feel.
- Take that back.
(grunting)
this is what happens when
you believe in true love.
Idiot.
- Is she always like this?
- No, no, she's usually meaner.
- [Man] Whiskey Cavalier,
special sneak preview after the Oscars.
Series premiere, Wednesday
10/9 central on ABC.
- [Announcer] The Oscars
on ABC brought to you by,
Google.
(energetic orchestral music)
(audience applauding)
From Rage Against the
Machine, here's Tom Morello.
(audience cheering)
(applauding)
- Movies, like music, can
do more than entertain.
A great movie can become
a part of the conversation
of history and like our next movie,
and the kind of songs I like to make,
it can do it with feedback,
noise and yes, anger.
Adam McKay's, Vice, is such a film.
Shredding the traditional biopic structure
with passion and humor, Vice
seeks to put a spotlight
on a man who avoided it his
whole career, Dick Chaney.
Brilliantly acted, the film
is a lesson about the past
that serves as a warning about
the present and the future.
War, greed, truth, lies, fatherhood, love,
torture and betrayal
all swirl around in Vice
with a hard backbeat
and a killer baseline.
Some will dig it, some
will cover their ears,
but everyone will do the one thing
the movie begs us to do, react.
This is Vice.
- [Man] So what's the plan?
- The plan is to take over the damn place.
- George, you're a kinetic leader.
You make decisions based on instinct.
(laughing)
- People always said that.
- I know what I'm gonna show
the world, true raw power,
of the American presidency.
- That's not something the
vice president really does.
- Oh, it is now.
- You need to remember
that if you have power,
people will always try
to take it from you.
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Please welcome
Elsie Fisher and Stephan James.
- It doesn't take a magic
wand to transform an actor
into a character whose look is memorable
and meaningful to the story.
- All it takes are this year's nominees
for achievement in
makeup and hair styling.
Border, Goran Lundstrom
and Pamela Goldammer.
Mary Queen of Scots, Jenny
Shircore, Marc Pilcher,
and Jessica Brooks.
Vice, Greg Cannom, Kate
Biscoe and Patricia Dehaney.
- And the Oscar goes to
Greg Cannom, Kate Biscoe and
Patricia Dehaney for Vice.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar and nomination
for Kate Biscoe and Patricia Dehaney,
the forth Oscar and 10th
nomination for Greg Cannom.
Oscars in this category have
been awarded since 1981.
(gentle orchestral music)
- Thank you Adam Herna,
our great director,
Adam McKay, Christian Bale,
what a, oh you're here. (laughing)
Go ahead.
- That's you.
Who's gonna read that?
- I already did, go ahead.
- Plan B, Gary Sanchez.
- The voting Academy members
and our fellow nominees
from the U.K. and Sweden, thank you.
- Christian Bale, what
you, you're fantastic.
You're so great to work
with and create with
and everything, thank you.
- Amy Adams, thank you
for bringing us up to your
level of commitment.
- Sam Rockwell and the 150
other SAG members, great job.
- Susan Matheson.
- Jeff Waxman and uh,
- Jennifer Madelov.
- Our DP, Greg Fraser,
our script, Dee Case.
- And Paula Williams,
Jamie Kelman, Adrian Mero,
Wesley Wauford, Christina Walt.
- Chris Gallager.
- Kenny Beyers.
- [Woman] Eric Porter and Brian Wade.
(applauding)
(gentle orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Please
welcome Brian Tyree Henry
and a nominee tonight for
actress in a leading role,
Melissa McCarthy.
(audience applauding)
(audience laughing)
- A rakish tilt to a hat,
the drape of fabric just so,
nuance and sophistication
are just two qualities--
(laughing)
of the most effective costume design.
- These artists create
a pettish of textiles
with authenticity, yet never
distract from the story.
Costume designers construct
the looks that ground
a character to a particular time and place
in the subtlest, subtlest of ways.
- [Brian] So true.
So true.
- So true.
- Here are the nominees for
achievement in costume design.
The Ballad of Buster Scruggs,
costume design by Mary Zophres.
Black Panther, costume
design by Ruth Carter.
The Favorite, costume
design by Sandy Powell.
Mary Poppins Returns, costume
Mary Queen of Scots, costume
design by Alexandra Byrne.
- And the Oscar goes to,
(audience laughing)
can't get it.
- Here, yeah,
okay.
- Get it, okay.
Black Panther, Ruth Carter.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the first Oscar
and third nomination for Ruth Carter.
She was previously
nominated in this category
for Malcolm X and Amistaad.
(gentle orchestral music)
- Wow, wow, I got it.
Wow, this has been a long time coming.
(laughing)
Spike Lee, thank you for my start.
I hope this makes you proud.
Woo.
(laughing)
Marvel may have created
the first black superhero,
but through costume design,
we turned him into an African king.
(applauding)
It's been my life's
honor to create costumes.
Thank you to the Academy.
Thank you for honoring African royalty
and the empowered way women
can look and lead on screen.
(applauding)
Thank you to my crews around the world
who helped bring Waconda to life,
our genius director, Ryan Cugler.
You are a guiding force.
Thank you for your trust
and understanding my role
in telling the African American story.
Adding vibranium to
costumes is very expensive
so thank you, Victoria,
Alonzo, Kevin Fahee,
Luis Esparzido, Jeffrey Chernov,
Bob Eiger and Nate Moore.
My career is built with
passion to tell stories
that allow us to know ourselves better.
This is for my 97 year old
mother watching in Massachusets.
Mom, thank you for teaching me
about people and their stories,
you are the original
super hero, thank you.
(applauding)
(gentle orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Coming up, Jennifer Lopez,
Chris Evans and Tyler Perry.
The award for cinematography and a look at
best picture nominee, a Star is Born.
Than later, Angela
Bassett and Javier Bardem,
plus a performance from Jennifer Hudson,
all here on the Oscars
at the Dolby Theater.
The Oscars on ABC, brought
to you by, Samsung,
meet the next generation, Galaxy S10.
And Walmart, see how we style the stars
behind the scenes in Walmart fashion.
(water running)
(menacing orchestral music)
(wooshing)
(screaming)
- [Woman] We style the
stars behind the scenes
in Walmart fashion.
- [Man] Perfect, let's try it again.
♪ It's taken over ♪
♪ There's no escape ♪
♪ You better get moving ♪
♪ Ready or not, slap the girl down ♪
♪ Here it comes now, get ready ♪
♪ Oh oh, oh oh, get ready ♪
♪ Get ready, get ready on now ♪
♪ Get ready, oh ♪
- Free, free, free, free.
(clinks)
(flames roar)
(exploding)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- [Man] That's right,
Turbotax free is free.
Free, free, free, free, free.
- Wow.
(smacking)
- Right?
- These cheesy bacon fries are tremendous.
- I know, crispy bacon is the best thing
to ever happen to the fries.
- (laughs) What?
It's a fry show, McDonald's
world famous fries,
featuring bacon.
- Or it is the crispy
bacon giving the fries
some street cred with
a whole new audience.
- I'm gonna let bacon think that.
- What was that?
I couldn't hear you
over the bacon ovation.
♪ Bacon, bacon, bacon, bacon ♪
- [Man] McDonald's classics with bacon,
only for a limited time.
Is it the best thing to
happen to our classics?
Order bacon, try for yourself and decide.
- [Man] To you, a filmmaker
of a future generation,
you and I, we're already
speaking to each other
from across time and I thought I'd
share this thought with you,
if you're burning to tell this story,
if you're seeing images and
passages in your mind's eye,
you have to make your movie.
You keep up your end of the conversation
and I'm looking forward to
hearing back from you soon.
Yours, Marty Scorsese.
- Good morning, friends.
I prayed with my mom
like five minutes ago.
She was like, go break a leg like you've
never braken it before.
- [Man] Let's see what you got.
♪ Going home tonight ♪
- [Announcer] The Oscars
will continue in a moment
here on ABC.
- [Man] Have you heard the
legend of old McClenden
who battled the bulls on
the bank single handed?
Rose like the tides to defile Poseidon,
evading the waves as they
raged from his trident.
McClenden braved roadways
where most men won't wander
to rescue the runaways from
the headmasters monster.
I sure would have loved
to see her that fine hour,
perhaps catch a glimpse of
the source of her power.
Make every day legendary.
- Dearest Britain,
- We love you.
- Maybe it's your big heart.
- Your sense of style.
- [Woman] Welcome to DA 100.
- [Man] DA 100 you're clear for take off.
- How you follow your own paths.
- You've led revolutions.
- Of all kinds.
- Yet you won't shout about it.
- Just not in your nature.
- Instead you'll quietly make history.
- Cake.
- Beds.
- Poetry.
- [Together] Trouble.
(singing)
- You love a lot of tea.
- [Woman] The best of Britain
from the moment you step on board.
- [Man] It's time to go, Toyota, go,
with a redesigned all new, 2019 Rav 4,
available with all wheel drive
and the latest multi-media system,
compatible with Apple CarPlay,
Amazon Alexa, and Wi-Fi.
Now, lease a Rav for only $219 a month
or finance with Toyota and get $1000
towards your down payment,
plus the peace of mind
that comes with having all these
advanced safety features standard.
Go, see your Toyota dealer today.
Toyota, let's go places.
- I'm live from the Oscars,
tonight and tomorrow on ABC 7.
- [Announcer] Please welcome
Jennifer Lopez and Chris Evans.
(applauding)
(cheerful orchestral music)
- Tonight is not only about
celebrating the people
in front of the camera,
it's also about recognizing
the artists who design the beautiful world
our characters inhabit.
- Let's take a look at the
incredible work they do
creating the overall
appearance of their films.
Here are tonight's
nominees for achievement
in production design.
Black Panther, production
design by Hannah Beachler
and set decoration by Jay Hart.
The Favorite, production
design by Fiona Crombie
and set decoration by Alice Felton.
First Man, production
design by Nathan Crowley
and set decoration by Kathy Lucas.
Mary Poppins Returns,
production design by John Myhre
and set decoration by Gordon Sim.
Roma, production design
by Eugenio Caballero
and set decoration by Barbara Enriquez.
- And the Oscar goes to,
Hannah Beachler, production design,
Jay Hart, set decoration,
from Black Panther.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar and nomination
for Hannah Beachler.
She is the first African
American to be nominated
in this category.
This is the first win and
3rd nomination for Jay Hart.
He was previously
nominated in this category
for Pleasantville and L.A. Confidential.
(cheerful orchestral music)
- Thank you, thanks, thank you.
- Thank you so much, can
you hold this for me?
- [Jay] Sure.
- I didn't even, okay, you're on my dress.
All right, New Orlean Jeremy.
Okay, I gotta put these on.
I don't even know where I put my speech
cause I put it in the phone
and now I can't find it.
I'm really shaking hard.
Okay. (hyperventilating)
I love you guys.
I want to thank all of the nominees
in this category for extraordinary worlds
that they built this year.
So an honor to be a part of that.
I want to thank the Academy,
thank you so much, Ryan Kugler.
(audience applauding)
I stand here stronger
than I was yesterday.
I stand here with agency and self-worth
because of Ryan Kugler
who not only made me
a better designer, a better
story teller, a better person.
I stand here because of this man
who offered me a different
perspective of life
who offered me a safe space,
who's patient and gave me
air, humanity and brotherhood.
Thank you, Ryan, I love you.
(applauding)
I'm stronger because of Marlon
who gave me the opportunity to do my best,
who supported the vision of this film
and lifted us up every day.
Victoria Alonzo, Keven
Fagey, Lou Despozito
and a man with the best
laugh ever, Nate Moore.
Thank you.
And he was sparked stronger because of
the Hart department crew
who led with their hearts
and brought their experiences, talent,
courage, humility and
hard work to the table.
Supervising art director, Allan Hook
and set decorator, Jay Hart, thank you.
I am stronger today because
of this wonderful cast,
who everyday, stepped into this world
and breathed life into it.
Because of Rue Carter and Rachel Morrison
and everything they did
behind the camera with me.
I'm stronger because of a woman who
supported me every day,
that I wanted to give up,
this is for you my friend,
Carole Trevino, rest in power. (crying)
I'm stronger because of
my family who supported me
through the roughest of times.
I give this strength to
all of those who come next
to keep going, to never give up
and when you think it's impossible,
just remember to say this peace of advice
I got from a very wise woman,
I did my best and my best is good enough.
Thank you.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Jay] I just want to thank my crew.
- [Announcer] Please welcome Tyler Perry.
(applauding)
- Community, we often
use that word to describe
who we are and what
connects all of us involved
in the different elements
that bring a film
from an idea in the writer's mind to
it's premier on the big screen.
Each person, each craft,
each discipline is
essential to that process.
Deep down, we know that.
We always have and in the end,
this truly collaborative community
comes together on a night like this
to celebrate this past year and
to look forward to the next.
It is a true honor for me
to present this next award
live on camera, not during
the commercial break,
thank you, academy. (laughs)
Here are the nominees for
achievement in cinematography.
Cold War, Lukasz Zal.
The Favorite, Robbie Ryan.
Never Look Away, Caleb Deschanel.
Roma, Alfonso Cuaron.
A Star Is Born, Matthew Libatique.
And the Oscar goes to,
Alfonso Cuaron, Roma.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Alfonso
Cuaron is the forth person
to receive four nominations
in four different
award categories for the same film.
This is his third Oscar
and 10th nomination.
(cheerful orchestral music)
- Thank you.
Wow, thank you so much.
It's an amazing honor.
Thank you, Academy.
To create a single frame
of film, as you well know,
requires the work of a lot of people,
very hard work, so I want
to thank Galiza Palizo
and Marina Perida before anybody else.
The amazing cast and
crew, Gabriel Rodriguez,
Selma Bolacelias, producers,
participant of Netflix.
Technicolor and every.
If this film was created
by my own memories,
the film was crafted through the memories
of what this great master
cinematography have given to us.
It's well known that
Billy Weidlers office,
there was a sign that said,
what would Ludwich have done?
And for me, it was what
would Chivo Woudeski
would have done, so this
is for you too Chivo
and thank you very much, Mexico,
to my family and Jonasbo
Guillermo, love you guys.
Thank you.
(applauding)
(gentle orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome Amelia Clark.
(applauding)
- The first nominee for original song
was composed for the
documentary feature, RBG.
Sung as a rallying cry, an anthem
and a personal promise, the song embodies
the seemingly endless
strength and commitment
of its subject supreme court justice,
Ruth Bader Ginsberg, a woman
who has spent her career
at the forefront of the fight
against gender discrimination.
Khalisi has nothing on her.
Justice Ginsberg, if you'd ever
like to borrow the dragons,
ring me.
Although the song's
subject is soft spoken,
its singer is a vocal powerhouse,
presenting its message with
the passion it deserves,
and now performing I'll Fight
by song writer, Diane Warren,
please welcome Academy Award
winner, Jennifer Hudson.
(audience applauding)
(gentle orchestral music)
♪ When you feel you're taking
all that you can take ♪
♪ And you're sure you're
never gonna catch a break ♪
♪ And the tears are rivers
running down your face, yeah ♪
♪ When your faith is low and
you've got no strength left ♪
♪ When you think you've
gone as far as you can get ♪
♪ And you're too undone
to take another step ♪
♪ Oh I will take up the struggle ♪
♪ Oh I know it's a fight ♪
♪ So I'll fight, fight that war for you ♪
♪ I'll fight, stand and defend you ♪
♪ Take your side, that's
what I'm here to do ♪
♪ I'll be there to be strong ♪
♪ Oh I'll keep on, keep on ♪
♪ I'll have your back when
your back's to the wall ♪
♪ And I'll catch your tears
when your tears fall ♪
♪ I will give it all, I
won't give up the fight ♪
♪ I'll fight, fight that war for you ♪
♪ Stand and defend you ♪
♪ I'll fight, that's what I'm here to do ♪
♪ I'll be there to be strong ♪
♪ Oh I'll keep on, keep on the fight ♪
♪ I'll, I'll fight ♪
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Keep watching
for more highlights
of this year's best picture nominees
and a performance by Bette Midler
and next, James McAvoy and Denai Gurira.
Then later, Angela Bassett
and Keegan Michael Key.
The Oscars on ABC, brought to you by,
Verizon, America's most reliable network.
- It's hard sometimes to be away.
(speaking Spanish)
My parents live in Mexico
and cannot travel anymore.
They're older now.
(speaking Spanish)
It's important for me
to feel like I'm there
and they can see my children grow.
(speaking Spanish)
Despite the distance, we
can communicate easily
and share special moments.
- [Man] There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best
network now always includes
Apple Music on us, starting
at only $40, only on Verizon.
(gentle twinkling music)
(humming engine)
(mellow rock music)
(cheering)
- [Woman] Every stage needs a star.
Every road needs a ruler.
Rise above with the Escalade
and the uncompromising Cadillac SUV's.
(beeping)
(muffled chatter)
- [Man] That was enough.
- [Man] This is a stunt test.
- Still rolling?
- [Woman] We style the
stars behind the scenes
in Walmart fashion.
- [Woman] Hey Google, are
there any hotels near by?
- [Siri] Bates Motel has a
rating of one out of five.
Are you looking for a room tonight?
- [Woman] I'd rather not.
- [Woman] Okay.
(speaking Spanish)
- Thank you very much.
Alejandro Inarritu.
- [Man] Paris, Rome, Prague,
put the spark back in your
relationship with romantic get aways.
You'll be swept off your
feet by old world charm
and the concussive force of RPG blow back.
(exploding)
(groaning)
- I so need a vacation.
- [Man] Romantic Detonations,
extensive government training required.
(dramatic orchestral music)
(screeching)
- How about a warning next time?
- Okay, we're here.
- We've assembled all of America's best
intelligence assets under one banner.
- [Man] My charm is like a virus.
Before you know it, boom, you're infected.
- So you're gonna give me a virus?
- I will stay on my side.
Do not worry.
Couch it is.
- [Announcer] Whiskey Cavalier,
special sneak preview after the Oscars,
series premier, Wednesday
10/9 central on ABC.
- [Announcer] Please
welcome Serena Williams.
(audience applauding)
- When we're young, we all have dreams
of what we can accomplish in life.
Having the dream is easy.
Making it come true is hard.
Whether that dream is becoming an actor,
a tennis player, or a singer,
like Ali in a Star Is Born.
In tonight's second
nominee for best picture,
we see through Ali's eyes,
the highs and the low
on the journey to stardom.
There's the rush of fame,
the pressure of success
and the heartache that
comes with sacrificing
love for career or career for love.
This is a Star Is Born.
♪ Don't want to feel another touch ♪
♪ Don't want to start another fire ♪
♪ Don't want to know another kiss ♪
♪ No other name falling off my lips ♪
♪ Don't want to give my heart ♪
♪ To another stranger ♪
♪ Oh I'll never love again ♪
(applauding)
- [Announcer] And now, please welcome
James McAvoy and Denai Gurira.
(gentle orchestral music)
- The nominees for sound editing this year
run the gamut.
- From the cacophony of
battle in Black Panther.
- And the arena rock of Bohemian Rhapsody.
- To the quiet tensions of home in Roma.
- And suspenseful
silence of a Quiet Place.
- And the utter silence
of space in First Man.
- Here are the nominees for
achievement in sound editing.
Black Panther, Benjamin A
Burtt and Steve Boeddeker.
Bohemian Rhapsody, John
Warhurst and Nina Hartstone.
(energetic rock music)
First Man, Ai-Ling Lee
and Mildred Iatrou Morgan.
(exploding)
A Quiet Place, Ethan Van
Der Ryn and Erik Aadahl.
(grunts)
(breaking glass)
Roma, Sergio Diaz and Skip Lievsay.
(rowdy crowd yelling)
- And the Oscar goes to Bohemian Rhapsody,
John Warhurst and Nina Hartstone.
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar and nomination
for John Warhurst and Nina Hartstone.
Bohemian Rhapsody is nominated
in five categories tonight
including best picture.
(energetic rock music)
- Wow, that's incredible.
We'd like to thank the Academy.
This truly is an honor,
especially in a category
with so many amazing sounding films.
Working on Bohemian Rhapsody
really was an honor.
I mean we got to work
with Queen for our day job
which was wonderful.
We'd like to thank all
of Queen and the team,
the full team for the,
just for the great music,
for all the support and yeah,
a special nod to Freddie as well.
(applauding)
And a quick shout out, so many
thanks, Steph, my kids, Nina.
- And I would like to thank
our full (inaudible) team,
all the people who are here and
also everyone back in London
who are now watching right now
and obviously, my husband
Kevin, who's up there,
my family, my kids, Noah, Lola and Eli,
my mom and dad who are looking after them.
Mom, we'll be home soon.
(applauding)
Thank you, thank you.
- And now it's time for the next award.
- Here are the nominees for
achievement in sound mixing.
Black Panther, Steve
Boeddeker, Brandon Proctor
and Peter Devlin.
(blasting)
Bohemian Rhapsody, Paul Massey,
Tim Cavagin and John Casali.
(singing)
First Man, John Taylor, Frank A. Montano,
Ai-Ling Lee and Mary H. Ellis.
(rumbling)
Roma, Skip Lievsay, Craig
Henighan and Jose Antonio Garcia.
(rowdy crowd yelling)
A Star Is Born, Tom
Ozanich, Dean Zupancic,
Jason Ruder and Steve Morrow.
(crowd yelling)
- And the Oscar goes to,
Bohemian Rhapsody, Paul Massey,
Tim Cavagin and John Casali.
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is a first Oscar win
for this sound mixing team.
Paul Massey has a previous nomination,
receiving his first for his
work on Legends of the Fall.
Tim Cavagin was previously
nominated in this category
for Baby Driver and this
is the first nomination
for John Casali.
(energetic rock music)
- Thank you.
Thank you Academy, huge honor.
Like to thank our producers, Graham King,
Dennis O'Sullivan, Ted Guillano from Fox
and our whole sound crew, thank you.
A massive shout out to
Brian May and Roger Taylor.
Thank you so much for your
music and for your collaboration
and your support and I would like to
dedicate this to my kids,
Shawn, Andrew, Sophie, Taylor,
I love you all, thank you.
- I want to thank my wife, my kids,
Olivia, Joe, Steven and
Jemma and all of my team
and for this really, for Chris
Murphy, my boom operator,
whose put up with me for
14 years, thanks mate.
Thank you.
- I'd like to thank team Trickanem,
our circuit, everyone else
who worked on the sound
in this incredible movie.
To my mom and dad, my amazing brothers
and to my friends back in
Odium watching tonight.
Thank you.
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Now the award
for foreign language film
and a performance by Bette Midler.
Then later, we find out who
wins for supporting actor.
Will it be Mahershall Ali, Adam Driver,
Sam Elliot, Richard E.
Grant, or Sam Rockwell?
Plus, Lady Gaga and Bradley
Cooper take the stage.
- Dear film makers,
use your gifts to reach beyond
your wildest imagination.
Make a difference in this world.
Compassion is your best friend.
Say what you believe.
Your voice matters.
Take action.
I ask, if not you, who?
Thank you.
Katherine.
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Hey.
- [Man] Hey.
- [Woman] We style the
stars behind the scenes
in Walmart fashion.
- Do you have Brie?
- [Woman] So cute.
- Best buds.
Wait, who's that blurred
out there in the background?
Did you boca my child?
- Um, it was totally unintentional.
- Why do you hate Jacob?
- (laughing) What?
No, look, I can unboca, see?
Boca, unboca.
- Wow.
What kind of person boca's a child?
I would never boca your child.
Just so you know.
- [Man] Jessica was in
bed when you got home.
- Yeah, she was sound asleep.
- So you didn't get into a fight?
- No.
- When was the first time you hit Jessica?
- I didn't hit her, man.
Listen, I came in here
to help you guys out--
- Just hiding the beatings
til you knew she was leaving,
what?
- You got a hearing problem?
I told you I didn't hit her.
Listen, where is all this coming from?
I came in here of my own volition.
- Was she cheating on you?
- Piss off.
- Dammit.
- Are you back there?
Are you?
You'll never not get me, Maya.
I'm an innocent man.
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Please welcome
Oscar nominated actress,
Queen Latifa.
- It is an honor to be here to introduce
one of tonight's nominees for
best picture, The Favorite.
The film takes us to 18th century Britain
with a monarch lacking
the interest and maybe
the ability to lead.
Decision making is taken
over by an inner circle
that's infighting for
the ruler's affection.
As the stakes get higher,
we see corruption lead to the downfall
of one underling after another.
It's not easy being queen.
This is The Favorite.
- I hope you haven't found
your time with the queen
too tedious.
(rings bell)
(screaming)
- She seems quite lovely.
- [Woman] The queen is
an extraordinary person.
- [Woman] You're so beautiful.
If I were a man, I would ravish you.
(screams)
(laughing)
- And stand up the other way.
- You're jealous.
- [Woman] She is a viper.
(slaps)
- I am on my side, always.
- Stop it.
Stop!
- [Woman] Oh it is fun
to be queen sometimes.
- [Woman] Do you actually
think you have won?
- Why would I?
- Take your shot.
(fires gun)
(splats)
(applauding)
(cheerful orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Please welcome
Academy Award nominated
actress, Angela Basset
and Academy Award winning
actor, Javier Bardem.
(speaking a foreign language)
- Members of the movie academy
come from across the globe
so it is truly fitting
that this year, foreign language films
are not just recognized in this category,
but in almost every category.
- Exactly.
- Here are the nominees for
best foreign language film.
From Lebanon, Capernaum,
directed by Nadine Labaki.
From Poland, Cold War,
directed by Pawel Pawlikowski.
From Germany, Never Look Away,
directed by Forian
Henckel von Donnersmarch.
From Mexico, Roma,
directed by Alfonso Cuaron.
From Japan, Shoplifters,
directed by Hirokazu Kore-Eda.
- And the Oscar goes to,
- [Together] Roma.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the
ninth movie from Mexico
to be nominated and the
first to win the Oscar
for foreign language film.
(gentle orchestral music)
- Thank you.
Am I going to get some
(inaudible) as well?
Well, thank you, Yaliza.
Thank you Marina.
Thank you Gabriela, Nico,
all the cast and crew.
I grew up watching
foreign language films and
learning so much from them
and being inspired,
films like Citizen Kane,
Jaws,
(audience laughing)
Rashamon, The Godfather and Breathless.
When asked about the new wave,
Claude Sharolt said, there are no waves,
there's only the ocean and I think that
the nominees tonight
have proven that we are
part of the same ocean.
I want to thank my family, Mexico,
for being the beach where
this film comes from
and also to Ormo, Boo and
Hernanz to be the current
that pushes my drift.
Thank you so much.
(applauding)
(cheerful orchestral music)
- [Announcer] And now,
dropping into the Oscars
from above, please welcome
Keegan Michael Keene.
(Mary Poppins orchestral music)
- Thank you.
This thing.
(scattered laughter)
This evening's next nominee
for best original song
was written by Mark
Shaman and Scott Whitman
for the film Mary Poppins Returns.
In addition to lifting the
Bank's children's spirits
through a series of magical adventures,
Mary Poppins offers comfort and compassion
with this tender lullaby,
underscoring the notion
that a loved one who is lost
can still be very much present.
Performing the Place
Where Lost Things Go with
Mark Shaman on piano, please
welcome the divine, Miss. M.
(audience applauding)
(cheering)
(gentle orchestral music)
♪ Do you ever lie awake at night ♪
♪ Just between the dark
and the morning light ♪
♪ Searching for the
things you used to know ♪
♪ Looking for the place
where the lost things go ♪
♪ Do you ever dream or reminisce. ♪
♪ Wondering where to find
what you truly miss ♪
♪ Well maybe all those
things that you love so ♪
♪ Are waiting in the place
where the lost things go ♪
♪ Memories you've shared
gone for good you feared ♪
♪ They're all around you still
though they've disappeared ♪
♪ Maybe to the moon or
maybe somewhere new ♪
♪ Maybe all you're missing
lives inside of you ♪
♪ So when you need a
touch and loving gaze ♪
♪ Gone but not forgotten
is the perfect phrase ♪
♪ Smiling from a star
that she makes glow ♪
♪ Trust she's always there
watching as you grow ♪
♪ Find her in the place
where the lost things go ♪
(gentle orchestral music)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Coming up, a
look at best picture nominee,
Black Panther, the Oscars for film editing
and best supporting actor, Michael Keaton
and a performance of
Shallow by Oscar nominees,
Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper.
And later, Charlise Theron, Casey Musgrays
and Laura Dern here at the Dolby Theater.
♪ When I was just a little girl ♪
♪ I asked my mother, what will I be ♪
- Will I be pretty?
♪ Will I be pretty ♪
Will I be rich?
♪ Will I be rich ♪
Is what she said to me.
♪ Is what she said to me ♪
♪ Que sera sera, whatever
will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
- [Man] To a future filmmaker,
your film will speak to
many with a singular voice.
Ask yourself what you have to say,
and then say it in ways
that are unique to you.
Recognize when lightening strikes
even if it's not what you planned.
Always stay humble before the craft.
And the most important thing,
pick up a camera and get going.
Now you're a filmmaker.
Jim Cameron.
(twinkling)
(phone rings)
- [Man] Hey, we need
the copper two in now.
- Allen, is that you?
- [Allen] You know who it is.
- Oh,
- [Allen] What?
- Allen,
- [Allen] Yeah.
- Reception's (hissing)
- [Allen] That's a noise
you're making with your mouth.
- You need to enunciate, I can't hear you.
- [Allen] I know you can hear me.
You owe me.
- [Woman] With XT4 technology,
make your escape, whatever it takes.
Rise above with XT4 and the
uncompromising Cadillac SUV's.
(gentle orchestral music)
- [Radio] Hey, we need an assist.
- Cut.
- [Woman] We style the
stars behind the scenes
in Walmart fashion.
- [Man] Hey when's lunch?
- Good morning, America.
I can't sleep anymo'.
I can't believe it's the day of.
♪ Coming home tonight ♪
- [Man] Here comes some energy.
- (screams) Okay.
♪ Starts to fly into the morning ♪
- [Announcer] The Oscars
will continue in a moment
here on ABC.
(cheerful strumming music)
♪ Oh I, I don't know the reason why ♪
♪ I found the answer looking in your eye ♪
♪ Cause I'll tell you
everything about living free ♪
♪ Cause I'll tell you everything ♪
- [Man] Introducing your
passport to adventure,
the all new Passport, from Honda.
- [Woman] You, all of you, how you live,
what you love, that's what inspired us
to create America's
most advanced Internet,
Internet that puts you in charge,
that protects what's important,
but handles everything
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond Wi-Fi, this is X-Fi,
simple, easy, awesome.
Xfinity, the future of awesome.
- [Man] It's a deadly blind
spot right under your nose,
tonight after the Oscars.
- [Announcer] Please welcome Trevor Noah.
(gentle orchestral music)
(audience applauding)
- Black Panther may be an African hero,
but his story and his
appeal are universal.
I know this personally
because of all the people
who constantly come up to
me and say, Waconda forever.
(audience laughing)
Everywhere in the world, my
African friends are like,
Waconda forever.
In France, I've had people
say, Hello Trevor Noah,
you say Waconda forever, no?
Even backstage, Mel
Gibson came up to me like,
Waconda forever.
He said another word after that,
but the Waconda part was nice.
(audience laughing)
Growing up as a young boy in Waconda,
I would see King Techalla
flying over our village
and he would remind me
of a great Cossa phrase,
(speaking foreign language)
which means, in times like these,
we are stronger when we fight together
than when we try to fight apart.
This is best picture
nominee, Black Panther.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Man] I know that we have
the right king, (inaudible).
(screaming)
(shattering glass)
- You're a good man
with a good heart
and it's hard for a good man
to be king.
(battle cry)
(whooshing)
- The black panther lives.
- [Woman] You get to
decide what kind of king
you are going to be.
- Waconda forever!
- [Group] Waconda forever!
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Please welcome
Oscar nominated actor,
Michael Keaton.
(gentle orchestral music)
- If you think of shooting
a movie and making a movie
as the same thing,
you've overlooked one of
the most important elements
of film making, the editing.
Editors infuse a film with rhythm,
they build suspense
and they create moments
that otherwise would not have existed
and as an actor, they can make things
like your performance a
whole lot better, trust me.
(audience laughing)
And here are the nominees for
achievement in film editing.
Black Klansman, Barry Alexander Brown.
Bohemian Rhapsody, John Ottman.
The Favorite, Yorgos Mavropsaridis.
Green Book, Patrick J. Don Vito.
Vice, Hank Corwin.
And the Oscar goes to,
Bohemian Rhapsody, John Ottman.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar and nomination
for John Ottman.
(orchestra playing Queen)
- He just asked if I would
like this and I said,
sure, my mom would like it, who is here.
Over there, she's 85 years old.
Wow, you get up here and
you completely blank.
This film, I always like to say,
the entire cast and
crew like to always say,
was a labor of love and
I think Freddie Mercury,
in a way, kind of brought us all together
from wherever he is and,
just like he did his audience
and I just am so thankful
for everyone bonding together
and supporting each other and trusting me
and I want to, there's too
many people to thank of course.
I'm looking at Rami (mumbles)
right looking at me,
better thank me. (laughs)
Got the band over here,
thank you so much, Brian May
and Roger Taylor and not to mention,
of course, Graham King
and Dennis O'Sullivan,
two of the hardest working
and committed producers
I've ever worked with my life
and lastly, this goes to my parents
on their fireplace mantle because
they encouraged me to do
whatever I wanted to do
when I was a kid whether
it was writing music,
which was a mystery to them or
making films in their garage
on Nominator Way in San Jose, California.
So as Freddie's father would say,
good thoughts, good words,
good deeds, thank you.
(applauding)
(cheerful orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Please welcome, Daniel Craig
and Academy Award winner, Charlise Theron.
(applauding)
- As actors, we show up, we work hard
and hopefully we take our job seriously
without taking ourselves too seriously.
(clears throat) And seriously,
Charlise Theron can kick my ass.
We aspire to transform ourselves
into the characters we
play and to transport
the movie goer in the process.
- Among a sea of brilliant
performances each year,
certain of them stand
out for their artistry,
their honesty, and the
masterful choices made
in interpreting their role.
We honor those individuals tonight.
- Here are the nominees
for performance by an actor
in a supporting role.
Mahershala Ali, Green Book.
- I just put the Attorney
General of the United States
in an incredibly awkward position.
- So what, that's what
the guy gets paid for.
What else does he got to do?
- That man and his brother
are trying to change this country.
That's what else he got to do.
Now he thinks I'm some kind of,
calling from some backwoods swamp jail
asking to attenuate assault
charges, who does that?
Garbage, that's who.
(applauding)
- [Daniel] Adam Driver, Black Klansman.
- I'm Jewish, yes, but
I wasn't raised to be.
It wasn't part of my life,
I never thought much about being Jewish,
nobody around me was Jewish.
You know, I wasn't going
to a bunch of bar mitzvahs.
I didn't have a bar mitzvah.
I was just another white kid
and now I'm in some
basement, denying out loud.
(chuckling)
(applauding)
- [Daniel] Sam Elliott, A Star Is Born.
- It ain't your fault.
It just isn't.
You know whose fault it was?
Jack.
That's it.
No one else.
(applauding)
- [Daniel] Richard E. Grant,
Can You Ever Forgive Me?
- She not here anymore, she died.
- She did?
That's young.
- Maybe she didn't die,
maybe she just moved back to the suburbs.
I always confuse those two.
That's right, she got
married and had twins.
- Better to have died.
- Indeed.
(applauding)
- [Daniel] Sam Rockwell, Vice.
- You're one of the most
experience guys around, you and I.
Jump on board and be my vice?
- I'm honored.
- Don't be honored, say
yes, Mr. Brass Tacks.
- I'll have to say uh, no.
- Dick, come on, we'll have a lot of fun.
What are you doing right now?
You in the private sector?
- [Dick] Yeah.
- Come on, I know you love politics.
- No George.
- Let's go.
- [Dick] Not gonna happen.
- Come on now. (chuckling)
(applauding)
- And the Oscar goes to,
Mahershala Ali.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the second Oscar
and second nomination for Mahershala Ali.
He took home his first
Oscar in this category
for Moonlight.
(cheerful orchestral music)
- Academy, thank you.
I want to thank Dr. Shirley for
just trying to capture his essence.
Trying to capture Dr. Shirley's essence
pushed me to my, my ends and um,
which is a reflection of the person he was
and the life that he
lived and I thank him.
I thank my partner, Vigo,
extraordinary working with you.
(applauding)
Peter Fairly, I thank
you for your leadership
and your guidance and
for also giving us space,
like really giving us space to work it out
and coming in and tweaking
and really appreciate it, love you.
Octavia Spencer.
(applauding)
Chris Bowers, my double.
I want to dedicate this to my grandmother
who has been in my ear my entire life,
telling me that, if at
first I don't succeed,
try, try again, that I could
do anything I put my mind to,
always, always pushing
me to think positively
and I know that I would
not be here without her,
that she has got me over the
hump every step of the way.
I thank my wife and my daughter, Barrie.
I thank Universal, Participant, Amblin,
everyone who contributed
and helped with our movie.
Again, thank you so much, appreciate it.
(applauding)
(cheerful orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Coming up next,
the award for animated feature.
Then later, a look at
Bohemian Rhapsody and Roma
and a performance of
Shallow from A Star Is Born.
Last year, movies took us across the globe
from the magic of Singapore
to the mysteries of Africa,
enchanting us with the joy of travel.
(twinkling music)
(inspirational orchestral music)
(cheerful piano music)
- Bonvoy.
(sniffing)
- Ha!
- Bonvoy.
- [Group] Bonvoy.
(screaming)
- Bonvoy.
(swishing)
- [Man] Bonvoy!
(sports announcer calling play)
- [Group] Bonvoy!
- Bonvoy.
- [Group] Bonvoy.
- [Woman] Bonsai?
- [Woman] Bonvoy.
- Bonvoy.
- Bonvoy!
(echoing)
- [Man] Discover the
new language of travel.
Marriott Bonvoy, 30 hotel brands,
endless experiences, rewards re-imagined.
- [Announcer] Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome Academy Award
nominated actress, Laura Dern.
(applauding)
(cheerful orchestral music)
- Growing up in Los Angeles,
can you believe it was only a dream
that there would ever be a place
where people could go
to immerse themselves
in the passion and magic of movies?
Even as a child of
actors, there was nothing,
trust me, but guess what?
The dream is happening.
When we enter the new Academy
Museum of Motion Pictures,
(audience applauding)
we will open a door and walk
into the technicolor land of Oz.
We will travel through the
animated world of Miazaki,
perhaps encounter the shark from Jaws,
and see the ruby red slippers.
The dream is a reality, not
just for the child in me,
but for all of us from all
around the world, coming soon.
(audience applauding)
- [Announcer] Please welcome, Michelle Yo
and Oscar nominated composer
and producer, Ferrell Williams.
(gentle orchestral music)
- The Bible says, when I was a child,
I spoke as a child, I
understood as a child,
I thought as a child
and when I became a man,
I put away childish things.
- When we move through adulthood,
we look back fondly on
those simpler times,
the creativity we
exhibited, our fearlessness,
how we approached new things with wonder.
- The films nominated
for best animated feature
possess the ability to move us all.
No need to put things away,
but instead embrace and
enjoy a shared experience.
- Here are the nominees for
best animated feature film.
Incredibles 2, Brad Bird, John Walker
and Nicole Paradis Grindle.
Isle of Dogs, Wes Anderson, Scott Rudin,
Steven Rales and Jeremy Dawson.
Mirai, Mamoru Hosoda and Yuichiro Saito.
Ralph Breaks The Internet, Rich Moore,
Phil Johnston and Clark Spencer.
Spider-man: Into the Spider-verse,
Bob Persichetti, Peter
Ramsey, Rodney Rothman,
Phil Lord and Christopher Miller.
- And the Oscar goes to,
(laughing)
Maybe you were right.
- [Together] Spider-man:
Into the Spider-verse.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Michelle] Wait, we
have to read the names.
- [Ferell] Oh yeah,
yeah, yeah, sorry, sorry.
- [Michelle] Bob Persichetti,
Peter Ramsey, Rodney Rothman--
- [Ferrell] Phil Lord
and Christopher Miller.
- [Michelle] Woo! (laughing)
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar and nomination
for Bob Persichetti, Peter
Ramsey, Rodney Rothman,
Phil Lord and Christopher Miller.
- [Man] There's a lot of us.
- [Man] Wow.
- [Man] Hey um,
- What.
- Thank you, Academy.
- Thank you Sony.
We share this with our fellow producers,
cast, crew, there's 800 filmmakers
who push boundaries and
took risks to make people
feel powerful and seen.
- So when we hear that somebody,
somebody's kid was watching the movie
and turned to them and
said, he looks like me,
or they speak Spanish like us,
we feel like we already won.
(audience applauding)
- To our audience, thank you so much.
We love you and we just want,
we want you all to know, we
see you, you're powerful.
This world needs you, okay?
This world needs you so please,
we're all counting on you.
Thank you.
(applauding)
- On behalf of everyone
that made this movie,
we want to thank our
families who stayed with us
for four years on this, this is for you.
We love you all.
(audio cut out)
(cheerful orchestral music)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Please
welcome Casey Musgraves.
(audience applauding)
- The Ballad of Buster
Scrugs brought new life
into westerns with its mix of satire,
sentiment, realism and romance.
All of these qualities are on display
in this haunting song.
It's fresh, but yet you feel like
you've heard it your whole life.
It could have been an absurd
and comical moment in the film,
but the song elevates it
into something authentic
and beautiful.
Here are the wonderful Gillian
Welch and David Rollings
with their Oscar nominated song,
When a Cowboy Trades His Spurs For Wings.
(audience applauding)
(cheerful strumming music)
♪ Let me tell you buddy ♪
♪ There's a faster gun ♪
♪ Coming over yonder when tomorrow comes ♪
♪ Let me tell you buddy ♪
♪ And it won't be long ♪
♪ Til you find yourself singing ♪
♪ Your last cowboy song ♪
♪ Yippee kai yai yay,
when the roundup ends ♪
and the campfire dims ♪
♪ Yippee kai yai yay, he shalt be saved ♪
♪ When a cowboy trades
his spurs for wings ♪
(gentle strumming music)
♪ Yippee kai yai yay, I'm glory bound ♪
♪ No more jingle jangle,
I lay my guns down ♪
♪ Yippee kai yai yay, he shalt be saved ♪
♪ When a cowboy trades
his spurs for wings ♪
(applauding)
(cheerful western music)
- [Announcer] Coming up, highlights from
best picture nominees Bohemian Rhapsody,
Roma, Black Klansmen and Green Book,
plus Mike Meyers and Dana
Carvey together on stage.
Chadwick Boesman,
Constance Woo, Bree Larsen,
Samuel L. Jackson, Lady
Gaga and Bradley Cooper.
The Oscars on ABC, brought to you by,
the uncompromising Cadillac SUV's.
(twinkling music)
(bell rings)
(cheering)
(mellow rock music)
(beeps)
(engine starts)
- [Woman] May the road
rise up to meet you.
May the wind be at your back.
Rise above in the
uncompromising Cadillac SUV's.
(phone rings)
- Hello?
- [Man] Hello, are you ready?
- Yes.
- [Man] What door am I at?
- Patio door, police are
on their way, see ya.
(sighs)
(crickets chirping)
(dog barking)
(dramatic percussion music)
(whooshing)
- [Man] I understand
you're a brother of mine.
- [Man] Yeah, yeah, glad to meet ya.
(soft dramatic orchestral music)
- [Man] I heard you paint houses.
(clanking)
- [Man] Yes, I do.
(soft dramatic orchestral music)
(gentle orchestral music)
(walking footsteps)
(speaking French)
- [Man] That's cut.
(alarm rings)
- [Woman] Copy that.
- [Woman] We style the
stars behind the scenes
in Walmart fashion.
- [Man] Empire actor, Jussie Smollett
took advantage of the
pain and anger of racism
to promote his career.
- [Announcer] GMA exclusive,
Chicago's top cop,
his first interview in the stunning
Jussie Smollett investigation.
What will he say now?
Tomorrow on Good Morning America.
- [Announcer] The Oscars
will continue in a moment
here on ABC.
(cheerful strumming music)
- Hey, Mercedes, how about
letting your hair down a little?
- Hey, Mercedes, how about a car
for people who don't play golf?
- How about something my
dad would never drive?
- Come on, guys, seriously?
- It's time for a change.
- Mix it up a little.
- Hey, Mercedes, how about a
car I can park in the street?
- How about something for a guy who
doesn't want a corner office?
(speaking Spanish)
- Hey Mercedes,
- Not everyone went to law school.
- You've heard of a touch screen, right?
- Hello?
- Hey Mercedes, I don't even own a tie,
you think I need a mahogany dashboard?
- Hey Mercedes, can you make
it a little cooler in here?
- [Computer] I'm setting the
temperature to 68 degrees.
- Hey Mercedes, is Tai Kitchen open?
- [Man] We hear you.
We made a car that does too, the A-Class,
all new thinking for an
all new class of Mercedes,
starting at $32,500.
(energetic electronic music)
- I've talked on this phone
through the happiest times
of my life and through the
saddest times of my life,
but I never dreamed in a thousands years
it would save my life.
Boom.
I fell 22 feet, completely
shattered my pelvis.
In the middle of the
woods, I called my wife.
She thought I was joking.
I said, man, I'm not (laughing).
I was so lucky that day, saved my life.
- [Man] There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best
network now always includes
Apple Music on us, starting at only $40,
only on Verizon.
- Wind is our big story,
how strong they get,
coming up right after the Oscars.
- I think we'll go with
a little Bohemian Rhapsody, gentlemen.
- Good call.
♪ Mama mia, mama mia ♪
♪ Mama mia, let me go ♪
♪ Beezlebub has a devil put aside for me ♪
♪ For me ♪
(energetic rock music)
- [Announcer] Ladies and
gentlemen, please welcome
Mike Meyers and Dana Carvey.
(audience cheering)
(screaming)
- We're not worthy!
- I think I'm gonna hurl.
- Don't hurl cause if you honk, I'll spew.
(audience laughing)
- And if you spew, I'll blow chunks.
So I shall not hurl.
- Good call, good call.
(laughing)
(applauding)
- [Dana] But seriously.
- Bohemian Rhapsody played a large part
in the success of Wayne's World.
We're humbled to be associated
with that brilliant song.
- It's our pleasure to
introduce a best picture nominee
that celebrates the
life of Freddie Mercury
through the genius of Queen's music.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
- [Together] Bohemian Rhapsody!
(applauding)
- What is it like singing
for all those people?
- And I know they're listening.
♪ Aye oh ♪
I'm not afraid of anything.
♪ We are the champions ♪
- No one will play a queen.
- Fortune favors the band.
- Thoughts, good words, good deeds,
that's what you should aspire to.
(people talking)
- Just need a bit of time.
- But I don't have time.
♪ Aye oh ♪
Aye oh.
(energetic orchestral music)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Please welcome
Aqua Fina and John Mullany.
(energetic orchestral music)
- Oh my god, John.
- Oh my god.
- You're here, too.
That's good.
- Yeah, they told me back stage, like,
you're gonna do this with
Aqua Fina and I was like,
- [Together] Thank god,
I'm not presenting alone.
- This is my first time
ever at the Oscars,
like ever, ever.
- This is my first time
ever at the Oscars too.
- Oh my god.
- Yes!
- Yes.
I'm having a panic attack.
- I am so scared.
Why am I so scared right now?
- I don't know.
- It's like you see
these commercials and you're like,
oh, it's Hollywood's biggest night
and I'm always like, whatever, shut up.
And now I'm here and
like, this is Hollywood.
- This is Hollywood's biggest night.
It's a big night.
- I want these people
to like me to a degree
that I find embarrassing.
- Yeah, who were you most nervous to see?
Because when I walked out,
I saw Spike Lee and I was like, what?
- That's what you said?
- Yeah, I was, no, I was
like, hey Spike. (chuckles)
- That's great.
(laughing)
Do you know who I saw,
do you know who I saw
and I legit freaked out?
- Who, who?
- Jordan Peale.
- Don't you know him?
- Yeah, that's why it's weird.
- All right, this is awesome.
Let's do this.
We are here to present the
award for best animated short.
- Dude, they gave us one of the big ones!
- It's a big one.
- All right.
(laughing)
Here are the nominees for
best animated short film.
(squishing)
Animal Behavior, Alison
Snowden and David Fine.
(barking)
Bao, Domee Shi and Becky Neiman-Cobb.
Late Afternoon, Louise Bagnall
and Nuria Gonzalez Blanco.
One Small Step, Andrew
Chesworth and Bobby Pontillas.
Weekends, Trevor Jimenez.
- And the Oscar goes to, Bao.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar and nomination
for Domee Shi and Becky Neiman-Cobb.
Academy Awards in this category
have been presented since 1932.
(energetic orchestral music)
- Okay, um,
holy--
- It's our first time too.
- Yeah, it's our first
time too, oh my gosh.
Thank you to the Academy and thank you
to my fellow nominees.
Thank you for supporting shorts.
To all of the nerdy girls out there
who hide behind their sketchbooks,
don't be afraid to tell
your stories to the world.
You're gonna freak people out,
but you'll probably connect with them too
and that's an amazing feeling to have.
Thank you to Pete Doctor for
believing in my weirdness
and for giving me a voice at the studio
and thank you, of course, to you know,
my mom and my dad, my
muses and my partner Darren
for being with me through all of this
and being my human stress ball, thank you.
- We want to thank the entire Bao crew.
They brought their heart to this short
and you can see it in every shot.
To everyone at Pixar,
you inspire us every day.
Disney for believing in us.
To my friends and family,
parents and sister,
I love you so much.
I got to make a short, help make a short
that was about a mother
just as I was becoming one,
so to my little bao, Lucy, and to Deanne,
none of this would be
possible without you.
I love you.
(applauding)
- Why are we still here?
Why, why are we here still?
- Are we doing another--
- We're doing another one!
- Oh, yes.
- Oh cool.
Oh.
- Documentary short subject?
- That's a good one.
- All right.
- Here are the nominees.
Black Sheep, Ed Perkins
and Jonathan Chinn.
End Game, Rob Epstein
and Jeffrey Friedman.
Lifeboat, Skye Fitzgerald and Bryn Mooser.
A Night At The Garden, Marshall Curry.
Period, End of Sentence, Rayka
Zehtabchi and Melissa Berton.
- And the Oscar goes to,
Period, End of Sentence.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar and nomination
for Rayka Zehtabchi and Melissa Berton.
(gentle orchestral music)
(crying)
- I'm not crying because I'm
on my period or anything.
I can't believe a film about
menstruation just won an Oscar.
(audience cheering)
Thank you.
Thank you, Netflix for
giving us a platform.
Thank you to my creative
partner, Sam Davis,
I share this with you, baby.
Thank you to my mom and my
sister, I love you guys.
To Lisa Tayback and Garret Shep,
to Gonite Monga and the women of Katigira,
know that you are empowering
women all over the world
to fight for menstrual equality.
(laughing)
- This film began because
high school students
here and our brave partners at Akton India
wanted to make a difference,
a human rights difference.
I share this award with the
Feminist Majority Foundation,
with Helen, Claire, Avery, Ruby, Sophie,
Charlotte, Carly, the
entire Pad Project team,
with the Oakwood School, I share this.
(laughing)
(applauding)
I share this with
teachers and with students
around the world.
A period should end a sentence,
not a girl's education.
(cheering)
(applauding)
(cheerful orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Some of the
biggest awards of the night
are ahead and right now,
we're heading to the backstage green room
to see the stars as they
get ready to go on stage
and where the winners come to celebrate
after their big moment.
Coming up next, Diego Luna, Jose Andres,
Paul Rudd, and Sarah Paulson,
plus a performance of Shallow by Lady Gaga
and Bradley Cooper.
The Oscars, on ABC, brought to you by,
Disney's new movie, The Lion King,
in theaters everywhere, July 19th.
(cheerful African music)
- [Man] It is time.
(energetic rhythmic percussion music)
(energetic rock music)
♪ It's taken over ♪
♪ There's no escape ♪
♪ You better get moving ♪
♪ Ready or not, slap the girl down ♪
♪ Here it comes now, get ready ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Get ready ♪
(beeping)
♪ Ready or not, get ready ♪
♪ Oh ♪
- [Woman] This is why you do it,
why you squeeze one more task
into your morning routine,
why you make bedtime just
as memorable as playtime.
For this, the big smiles
those little surprises can bring.
Kinder Joy is a two in one treat,
half smooth cocoa, sweet
cream and crispy wafers,
half mystery toy, now with
over 50 new surprises to build,
Kinder Joy, a little
surprise goes a long way.
(flames roaring)
(dramatic orchestral music)
- [Woman] We style the
stars behind the scenes
in Walmart fashion.
(bell rings)
♪ Tonight I'm gonna have
myself a good time ♪
♪ I feel alive ♪
♪ And the world ♪
♪ I'll turn it inside out, yeah ♪
♪ And float around in ectasy so ♪
♪ Don't stop me ♪
♪ Cause I'm having a good time ♪
♪ Having a good time ♪
♪ I'm a shooting star
leaping through the sky ♪
♪ Like a tiger defying
the laws of gravity ♪
♪ I'm a racing car passing
by like Lady Godiva ♪
♪ I'm gonna go, go, go ♪
♪ And there's no stopping me ♪
♪ I'm burning through the sky, yeah ♪
♪ 200 degrees, that's why
they call me Mr. Fahrenheit ♪
♪ I'm traveling at the speed of light ♪
♪ I wanna make a
supersonic man out of you ♪
♪ Don't stop me now ♪
♪ I'm having such a good time ♪
♪ I'm having a ball ♪
♪ Don't stop me now ♪
♪ If you wanna have a good
time, just give me a go ♪
♪ Don't stop me now ♪
♪ Cause I'm having a good time ♪
♪ Yeah I'm having a good time ♪
♪ I don't want to stop now ♪
- [Man] This is the
incredible talent you'll see
on American idol, next Sunday on ABC.
- [Announcer] The Oscars
on ABC brought to you by,
Walmart, see how we style
the stars behind the scenes
in Walmart fashion.
Please welcome Diego Luna
and Chef Jose Andres.
- Bueno noches a todos.
(laughing)
(speaking Spanish)
- I'm a chef, I follow the recipe.
- So, people of the world,
each person's life is a
recipe all on its own,
with different measures
of joy and sadness,
struggle and success, love and loss.
The results are unique every time
even though all of the
ingredients are universal.
- In Roma, Alphonso Corron
presents and honest and vital
portrait of the Mexico
city of his childhood,
a place full of contrast
and contradictions.
This is a story of lonely
women and absent men,
of painful class divisions
and racial dynamics,
but love is where everyone meets.
- And this beautiful intimate film,
one that gives a voice to the voiceless
reminds us of the
understanding and compassion
that we all owe to the invisible people
in our lives, immigrants and women
who move humanity forward.
(applauding)
(speaking Spanish)
(quiet strumming music)
(giggling)
(slow melancholy music)
(Spanish lyrics)
(chanting)
(slow melancholy music)
(Spanish lyrics)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Please welcome
Paul Rudd and Sarah Paulson.
(cheerful orchestral music)
(applauding)
- In Duck Soup, Chico Marks asks,
who are you going to
believe, me or your own eyes?
When it comes to visual effects,
the answer is not so simple.
- Today's effects artists collaborate
with every other department
to convince audiences
of even the most implausible realities.
This is the kind of magic
that allows the audience
to believe I was actually
obliterated by a truck in Bird Box.
- And the same kind of magic
that allows an audience
to believe that I am an actor.
(laughing)
- Here are this year's nominees
for achievement in visual effects.
Avengers Infinity War, Dan Deleeuw,
Kelly Port, Russell Earl and Dan Sudick.
Christopher Robin, Christopher Lawrence,
Michael Eames, Theo
Jones and Chris Corbould.
First Man, Paul Lambert, Ian Hunter,
Tristan Myles and J.D. Schwalm.
Ready Player One, Roger
Guyett, Grady Cofer,
Matthew E. Butler and David Shirk.
Solo: A Star Wars Story, Rob Bredow,
Patrick Tubach, Neal
Scanlan and Dominic Tuohy.
- And the Oscar goes to,
First Man,
(cheering)
Paul Lambert, Ian Hunter,
Tristan Myles and J.D. Schwalm.
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar and nomination
for Tristan Myles and J.D. Schwalm,
the second win and second time nominees,
Paul Lambert and Ian Hunter.
(gentle orchestral music)
- Oh my goodness, okay.
What a truly magnificent
moment, putting things
a little bit differently on
First Man so being recognized
by the Academy is all the more special.
Thanks goes to my visual
effects producer, Kevin Elam.
Also Jennifer Bell and
Bill Tolusy at Universal,
thank you to the
inspirational Damion Chazell
and
(applauding)
and our amazing cast
and all the incredible
heads of department, Linus,
Tom, Justin, Mildred,
Aileen, Nathan, Rose,
Ian, Josh, Mary and Donald
who made this film so, so memorable
and a big shout out to Shell
Izenrack, River Paulter
and all my people at Dean and
Frank who left, thank you.
- Thank you again, Damian Chezell,
my amazing effects team,
my wife, Erica, I love you,
my two boys, John and
James and my dad, Jim
who taught me how to put the
magic in movies, thank you.
- Thanks to the crew and to Dean Hank.
Without his hard work, we
wouldn't be stood up here tonight.
Also thanks to my wife,
Kirsty and our two children,
Isabella and Eloisa for all
their support over the years.
- And it's an honor and it's humbling
to honor Neil Armstrong
and all the men and women
of NASA, so thank you so much.
(shouting indecipherably)
(applauding)
(gentle strumming music)
(cheering)
(applauding)
♪ Tell me something girl ♪
♪ Are you happy in this modern world ♪
♪ Or do you need more ♪
♪ Is there something else
you're searching for ♪
♪ I'm falling ♪
♪ In all the good times I find
myself longing for change ♪
♪ And in the bad times I fear myself ♪
(audience cheering)
(applauding)
♪ Tell me something boy ♪
♪ Aren't you tired trying
to fill that void ♪
♪ Or do you need more ♪
♪ Ain't it hard keeping it so hard core ♪
♪ I'm falling ♪
♪ And all the good times I find
myself longing for change ♪
♪ And in the bad times I fear myself ♪
♪ I'm off the deep end,
watch as I dive in ♪
♪ I'll never meet the ground ♪
♪ Crash through the surface
where they can't hurt us ♪
♪ We're far from the shallow now ♪
♪ In the shallow, shallow ♪
♪ Hold, hold on ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I'm off the deep end,
watch as I dive in ♪
♪ I'll never meet the ground ♪
♪ Crash through the surface
where they can't hurt us ♪
♪ We're far from the shallow now ♪
♪ In the shallow, shallow ♪
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Coming up,
the Oscars for original
and adapted screenplays.
Then later, we'll find out
who brings home the Oscars
for best actor and
actress, plus Brea Larson,
Samuel L. Jackson, Tessa
Thompson, Chadwick Bosman
and Constance Woo, here on the Oscars.
The Oscars on ABC, brought to you by,
Verizon, America's most reliable network.
- I love my babies, love my boys.
Since I'm a truck driver, you know,
there's times that I'm gone
for like three weeks at a time.
Even if I'm 3000 miles away,
I'm connected with my boys.
Every day I can video chat with em.
I could be in the middle of Wyoming.
Even if I'm like way out here,
I can still reach my
kids, baby, you see me?
- [Boys] Hey daddy.
(laughing)
- [Man] There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best
network now always includes
Apple Music on us, starting at only $40,
only on Verizon.
(beeping)
(inaudible chatter)
(people talking)
- [Man] This is a stunt test.
- Still rolling?
- [Woman] We style the
stars behind the scenes
in Walmart fashion.
- You are gonna love Fabio.
You know I was married.
- I can't do this.
- We're making a movie.
- Oh.
- Where's that smile?
- I love you.
- Why is that so terrible?
- I'm in love with her.
- What comes next?
- Do it again.
(energetic rhythmic music)
- Daddy?
(dramatic orchestral music)
(cheerful piano music)
- Bonvoy.
(sports announcer calling a play)
- [Group] Bonvoy!
- [Group] Bonvoy.
- Bonvoy.
- Bonvoy!
(echoing)
- [Man] Discover the
new language of travel,
Marriott Bonvoy, 30 hotel brands,
endless experiences, rewards re-imagined.
- [Man] In one of television's
most groundbreaking roles,
Freddie Highmore is--
- I'm Dr. Shawn Murphy.
I have autism.
- [Man] The Good Doctor,
all new Monday on ABC.
- You are amazing in every single way.
I am sorry I didn't tell you more.
- I dare you to show the world
that you are not afraid of anything.
- You are not the best part of my life.
You are my life.
- I feel like every time
I go searching for answers
all we get are more questions.
- Don't you want to know the truth?
- [Man] A Million Little Things,
season finale, Thursday,
9/8 central on ABC.
- [Announcer] The Oscars
on ABC, brought to you by,
Marriott Bonvoy, rewards re-imagined.
Please welcome Kristine
Ritter and Kiki Lane.
(applauding)
(gentle orchestral music)
- This year's short films are innovative,
profoundly moving and
worthy of nominations
in every category.
- Set in locations around the world,
they show us the best
and worst in ourselves.
If you love movies, you
need to see these films.
- Here are the nominees for
best live action short film.
Detainment, Vincent
Lambe and Darren Mahon.
Fauve, Jeremy Comte and
Maria Gracia Turgeon.
Marguerite, Marianne Farley
and Marie-Helene Panisset.
Mother, Rodrigo Sorogoyen
and Maria del Puy Alvarado.
Skin, Guy Nattiv and Jaime Ray Newman.
- And the Oscar goes to,
- Yes!
- Skin, Guy Nattiv and Jaime Ray Newman.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar nomination
for Guy Nattiv and Jaime Ray Newman.
Academy Awards for live action short films
have been presented for over 80 years.
(cheerful orchestral music)
(screaming)
- Oh my god!
- Oh my god.
I moved here five years ago from Israel.
(speaking foreign language) Hi.
And my grandparents are
Holocaust survivors and you know,
the treatment they
experience in the Holocaust,
we see that everywhere
today, in America, in Europe
and this film is about education.
It's about teaching
your kids a better way.
- We dedicate this to our (screeching)
oh my god, our five month old baby
who's sitting at home with my parents,
watching this, we hope that you grow up
in a world where these things don't happen
because, because people learn
to love and accept each other.
I want to thank Andrew
Cobber, Sharon Ramon,
Tim Harms, all our team at ICM,
our Maven girls, Celine, Trudy,
or any of you out there
who are in (inaudible).
(yelling in a foreign language)
We love you!
Woo!
(applauding)
(cheerful orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Please welcome
Academy Award nominated actor,
Samuel L. Jackson and Academy
Award winner, Marie Larsen.
- Uh, first of all, Spike,
so glad you're sitting down.
After 18 consecutive home
losses, the Nicks won tonight.
I repeat, the Nicks won tonight
defeating San Antonio 130 to 118.
(laughing)
- And now to get back on script,
the legendary filmmaker, Frank Capra said,
script writing is the toughest
part of the whole racket,
the least understood
and the least noticed.
- Uh no, uh, we notice.
- Of course.
- Trust me, we notice.
- 100%.
- Bri and I don't show up on a movie set
and ad lib for 12 hours.
- Sometimes.
- We're not winging it.
We're not winging it, we
need words, we need words.
- Yeah.
- Which is why we truly appreciate
what the late, great William Goldman said
about his craft, the latest, (laughing)
the easiest thing to do
on Earth is to not write.
- Truth.
(audience laughing)
- Luckily these writers
took the hard path.
They are the nominees
for original screenplay.
The favorite, written by
Deborah Davis and Tony McNamara.
First Reformed, written by Paul Schrader.
Green Book, Written by Nick Vallelonga,
Brian Currie, Peter Farrelly.
Roma, written by Alfonso Cuaron.
Vice, written by Adam McKay.
- Okay, all right.
(laughing)
And the Oscar goes to,
- (gasps) Nick--
- [Together] Nick Vallelonga,
Brian Currie and Peter
Farrelly for Green Book.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the first
Oscar and second nomination
for Nick Vallelonga, Brian
Currie and Peter Farrelly
who are also nominated in
the best picture category.
(cheerful orchestral music)
- I'd like to thank Universal Studios,
Dreamworks and Participant Media.
As writers, when you have Mercerali,
Viggo Mortenson and Linda Cartelini,
saying your lines, you pinch yourself,
consider yourself the luckiest writers
on the face of the Earth.
I want to thank the entire cast and crew,
my whole family, all my friends who have
put up with my career and particularly
George and Eileen Currie, best parents
anybody could ever have.
- They say if you want
to go somewhere fast,
go alone, if you want
to go far, go together.
I got a lot of people
to thank, starting with
the entire state of Rhode
Island, thank you very much.
I want to thank Viggo,
Mahershale and Linda,
we have nothing without
you guys, I mean nothing.
Also I want to thank my wife, Melinda,
my kids, Bob and Ap up
there, Richard Lovett,
Joe Mann, Jeff Oakens, Cindy
Guessner, Peter Grossman,
Amanda Lundberg, Stacy
Langston, David Lindy,
Johnathan King, Robert
Kessel, Christina Kenilius,
J.B. Rogers, Charlie Wessler, Jim Burke,
Ted Virtue, John Porter, Tom
Cartsonus and Chinola Watches,
unbelievable, they're saving Detroit.
And finally, I want to thank my brother
and Bennett Yellen who
got me into this business.
I'm nothing without you.
Best people ever.
- This is an amazing
honor, thank you everyone
for voting for us, thank
you to the other nominees.
What an amazing category to be
in with such talented people.
This is an amazing room of filmmakers.
Embrace ourselves and love each other.
Thank you all, my mother
and father, dad, we did it.
(applauding)
(giggling)
- Okay.
- And now here are the nominees
for best adapted screenplay.
The Ballad Of Buster
Scruggs, written by Joel Coen
and Ethan Coen.
(inaudible) is based on
a story by Jack London.
The gal who got rattled
is inspired by a story
by Steward Edward White.
Black Klansman, written by Charlie Wachtel
and David Rabinowitz and
Kevin Willmott and Spike Lee,
based on the book by Ron Stallwell.
Can You Ever Forgive Me,
screenplay by Nicole Holofcener
and Jeff Whitty, based on
the book by Lee Israel.
If Beale Street Could Talk,
written for the screen
by Barry Jenkins, based on
the book by James Baldwin.
A Star Is Born, screenplay by Eric Roth
and Bradley Cooper and Will Fetters,
based on the 1954 screenplay by Moss Heart
and the 1976 screenplay
by John Gregory Dunn
and John Giddeon as Frank Pearson,
based on a story by William
Wellman and Robert Carson.
- Okay and the Oscar goes to,
(enthusiastic yelling)
- Charlie Wachtel, David
Rabinowitz and Kevin Wilmott
and Spike Lee.
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar and nomination
for Charlie Wachtel, David
Barinowitz and Kevin Wilmott.
It's the first win and fifth
nomination for Spike Lee.
- All right,
(cheering)
(applauding)
All right, (audio cuts out)
I want to thank Tanya, Jack Nesatchel.
The word today is arnie,
the date, the 24th,
the month, February,
which also happens to be
the shortest month of the year
which all happens to
be black history month,
the year 2019, the year 1619,
history, her story, 1619, 2019, 400 years,
400 years our ancestors were
stolen from mother Africa
and brought to Jamestown,
Virginia, enslaved.
Our ancestors worked the
land from Kansas City
to Des Moines, can't see at night.
My grandmother, (inaudible),
who lived to be 100 years young
who was a Spellman College graduate
even though her mother was a slave.
My grandmother who saved 50
years of social security checks
to put her first grandchild,
she called me Spikeypoo.
She put me through Morehouse
college and NYU Grad Film.
NYU!
(applauding)
Before the world tonight, I
give praise to our ancestors
who helped built this
country and was today
along with the genocide
of his native people.
We all connect with our ancestors.
We will have love, wisdom regained,
we will regain our humanity.
It will be a powerful moment.
The 2020 presidential
election is around the corner.
Let's all mobilize.
Let's all be on the right side of history.
Make the moral choice
between love versus hate.
Let's do the right thing.
You know I had to get that in there.
(cheering)
(applauding)
(cheerful orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Coming up, Barbara Streisand
and a look at the final
two best picture nominees,
Black Klansman and Green Book.
Then later, the Oscars
for best actor and actress
and Julia Roberts presents best picture.
Plus, Chadwick Mossman, Constance Woo
and Oscar winner Sam
Rockwell and Allison Jenny.
- You should just go to city college.
You know, with your work ethic,
just go to city college and then to jail
and then back to city college
and then maybe you pull yourself up--
- [Woman] You lift has arrived.
- Everybody to do everything-- (screaming)
♪ Aye oh, let's go ♪
- I can't believe it.
- That there's a lobster in our hot tub?
- Oh, you guys, there's a jet.
Oh, I needed this.
- No, I can't believe how easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
our car insurance with Geico.
We could have been doing
this a long time ago.
- So are you guys staying at the hotel?
- Yeah, we just got married.
- Oh, (laughing) congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, I'm afraid of commitment.
You know and being boiled alive.
Oh shoot. (splashing)
- [Man] Believe it, Geico
could save you 15% or more
on car insurance.
(gasping)
- [Lobster] That guy is the worst.
(gentle orchestral music)
- [Radio] Hey, we need an assist.
- Cut.
- [Woman] We style the
stars behind the scenes
in Walmart fashion.
- Hey, when's lunch?
- Here it is.
Show me the money.
- [Siri] Here you go.
(screaming)
- Yo, doesn't it make you
feel good just to say that?
Say it with me one time.
- [Announcer] The Oscars
will continue in a moment
here on ABC.
(humming engine)
- [Woman] The unknown beyond the horizon
that was once our frontier.
But today, a new frontier has risen
and this is the vehicle
crafted to conquer it.
Introducing the first of its
kind, Lexus UX and UX Export,
also available in hybrid four wheel drive.
Experience amazing at your Lexus dealer.
- [Woman] Everyone's gotta listen to mom.
When it comes to reducing the sugar
in your family's diet, Coke,
Dr. Pepper and Pepsi hear you
and we're working
together to do just that,
bringing you more great tasting beverages
with less sugar or no sugar at all.
Smaller portion sizes.
Clear calorie labels and
reminders to think balance
because we know mom wants what's best.
More beverage choices,
smaller portions, less sugar,
balaceUS.org.
- [Woman] You, all of you,
how you live, what you love,
that's what inspired us to create
America's most advanced Internet,
Internet that puts you in charge,
that protects what's important
and handles everything
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond wi-fi.
This is X-fi.
Simple, easy, awesome,
Xfinity, the future of awesome.
- [Man] It's a deadly blind
spot right under your nose,
tonight after the Oscars.
- [Announcer] Welcome back to the Oscars
at the Dolby Theater.
Tonight's band is led by
music director, Ricky Minor.
(gentle orchestral music)
and now, please welcome Tessa Thompson
and Michael B. Jordan.
(applauding)
- The score served as
a musical through-line
that impacts our feelings
in any given scene.
- Like when we hear this
Oscar winning score.
(Jaws theme song)
- I know it's time to take
my ass out of the water
because probably something bad
is gonna happen in the ocean.
- But wait, you can swim, right?
- Yeah, why would you ask me that?
- Just cause unfortunately a lot of people
don't know that about us.
- Ah, touche, touche.
Or uh, how about when we hear this.
(Titanic theme music)
That's good, right?
- We know people are going to fall in love
before something else
bad happens in the ocean.
A great score moves us as an audience.
- While reminding us
that really bad things
can happen in the ocean.
(laughing)
- Here are the nominees
for best original score.
(inspirational orchestral music)
Black Panther by Ludwig Goransson.
Black Klansman by Terence Blanchard.
If Beale Street Could
Talk by Nicholas Britell.
Isle of Dogs by Alexandre Desplat.
Mary Poppins Returns by Marc Shaiman.
- And the Oscar goes to,
- Ludwig Goransson.
- [Michael] Black Panther.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar and nomination
for Ludwig Goransson.
(cheerful orchestral music)
- (sighs) oh wow.
Thank you Ryan Cougar.
Ryan, Ryan, working with you has been
an incredible honor.
I remember 12 years ago we
were sitting in our dorm
at USC writing your first,
the score for your first short film
and we're here 12 years later,
you know, celebrating
one of the most important
cinematic moments in history.
I want to share this award
with all the incredible
African artists that I
worked with on the score,
Babamal, Masambadio, Magetso
and all the classical
musicians in London that
recorded on the score
and everyone else I want
to share this award with
my mom and dad and sister.
They insisted I play
guitar and my wife, Serena.
I love you so much, thank you.
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Please welcome Constance Woo
and Chadwick Boseman.
(applauding)
(cheerful orchestral music)
- Over the Rainbow and
the theme from Shaft.
- Mona Lisa and Lose Yourself.
- The Way We Were and Man or Muppet.
- Streets of Philadelphia and Remember Me.
The only thing these songs
could possible have in common
is the place they've earned in history
as Academy Award winners.
Tonight, another will join their ranks.
- This year's nominated
songs are as eclectic
and stylistically distinctive
as the stories they tell.
- Once again, here are
this year's nominees
for best original song.
All the Stars from Black Panther,
music by Kendrick Lamar,
Mark Sounwave Spears,
and Anthony Top Dawg Tiffith,
lyrics by Kendrick Lamar,
Sza and Anthony Top Dawg Tiffith.
I'll Fight from RBG, music
and lyric by Diane Warren.
The Place Where Lost Things
Go from Mary Poppins Returns,
music by Marc Shaiman,
lyric by Scott Wittman and Marc Shaiman.
Shallow from A Star Is
Born, music and lyric
by Lady Gaga, Mark
Ronson, Anthony Rossomando
and Andrew Wyatt.
When a Cowboy Trades His Spurs For Wings
from the Ballad of Buster Scruggs,
music and lyric by Gillian
Welch and David Rawlings.
- And the Oscar goes to,
let's see, okay,
Lady Gaga, Mark Ronson, Anthony Rossomando
and Andrew Wyatt.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the
first Oscar and nomination
for Mark Ronson, Anthony
Rossomando and Andrew Wyatt.
The first win and third
nomination for Lady Gaga
who is also nominated in the
leading actress category.
(cheerful orchestral music)
- Thank you so much. (crying)
Thank you so much to the Academy
for this wonderful honor.
Thank you to every single
person in this room.
Thank you to Mark Ronson,
to Anthony Rossomando,
to Andrew Wyatt, my co-writers,
I love them so much.
To my sister, my soulmate, I love you.
My family's here.
I love you mom and dad.
Bradley, there is not a
single person on the planet
that could've sang this
song with me, but you.
Thank you for believing in us.
Thank you so much.
(applauding)
If you are at home and
you're sitting on your couch
and you are watching this right now,
all I have to say is
that this is hard work.
I've worked hard for a long time
and it's not about, you know,
it's not about winning,
but what it's about
is not giving up.
If you have a dream, fight for it.
If there's a discipline for passion
and it's not about how
many times you get rejected
or fought you fall down
or you're beaten up,
it's about how many times you stand up
and are brave and you keep on going.
Thank you.
- Only because you can't
really thank yourself,
I think when you're in
the room with this person,
you don't really have to do too much,
so she acts, she writes,
she sings the song,
Lady Gaga, we salute
you, thank you for this.
(applauding)
(gentle orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Please welcome
the president of the Academy
of Motion Picture Arts
and Sciences, John Bailey.
(audience applauding)
- This evening we
celebrate the achievements
not only of our awards winners,
but all 212 nominees of the
Academies class of 2018.
We also pause to honor all those artists
who have left us since
our last awards ceremony,
the men and women whose
movies have so entertained
and inspired us.
Only a few of them can
be highlighted here,
but let's now give tribute
to all their extraordinary lives, works.
In this music of John Williams
with the Los Angeles
Philharmonics celebrating
its centennial year under the direction
of Maestro Gustavo Dudamel.
(audience applauding)
(somber orchestral music)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(audience applauding)
(quiet orchestral music)
- [Man] Dear tech.
- Dear tech.
- Let's talk.
- We have a pretty good relationship.
- [Man] You've done a lot
of good for the world.
- But I feel like you have the
potential to do so much more.
- Are you working for all
of us or just a few of us?
- Can we build AI without bias?
- AI that fights lies.
- AI that helps us see
the bias in ourselves?
- We need tech that helps
people understand each other.
- And understands my business.
- [Child] Dear tech.
- [Woman] Dear tech.
- Let's champion data
rights as human rights.
- Let's use blockchain
to help reduce poverty.
- Let's develop new solutions
with the help of quantum technology.
- Let's show girls that stem
isn't just a boy's club.
- Let's make a difference
in people's lives.
- Let's do it all.
- Together.
- Let's expect more from technology.
- Let's put smart to work.
(cheerful orchestral music)
(quiet mystical orchestral music)
(hissing)
(birds chirping)
(flapping)
(mystical orchestral music)
- [Man] There are moments
in a rock star's life
that define who he is.
- What'd you say your name was again?
- Elton.
♪ Hold me closer tiny dancer ♪
♪ Count the headlights on the highway ♪
This is never gonna last.
Let's enjoy it while we can.
(cheering)
♪ Hold me closer tiny dancer ♪
(menacing orchestral music)
- Hey.
- [Woman] We style the
stars behind the scenes
in Walmart fashion.
- Do you have Brie?
- I've talked on this phone through
the happiest times of my life
and through the saddest times of my life,
but I never dreamed in 1000
years it would save my life.
Boom.
I fell 22 feet, completely
shattered my pelvis
in the middle of the woods.
I called my wife.
She thought I was joking.
I said, man, I'm not. (laughing)
I was so lucky that day, saved my life.
- [Man] There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best
network now always includes
Apple Music on us, starting
at only $40, only on Verizon.
- When I'm in the field, I
need discrete protection.
The last thing I wanna worry
about, government leaks.
Now I don't have to.
- [Woman] Spy Tampons, government leaks
don't stand a chance.
(exploding)
- FBI, CIA under one banner.
- We've got to start treating
each other like we're family.
- [Woman] I don't do
emotional attachments.
- Well we accept the
love we think we deserve.
- Wow.
Gonna have to move fast
before this gets ugly.
- Not as ugly as that dress.
Frankie, you're gonna break him.
- [Frankie] I don't care.
(grunts)
(exploding)
- Cheers.
I am going to win you over.
- Definitely not.
- [Man] Whiskey Cavalier,
special sneak preview
after the Oscars, series premier,
Wednesday 10/9 central on ABC.
- [Woman] In November, the
Academy held the Governors Awards
where honorary Oscars were presented
to actress Sisily Tyson,
composer, Lalo Chifren
and publicist, Marvin Levee.
The Thalberg Award went to producers,
Kathleen Kennedy and Frank Marshall.
Kennedy is the first woman
to receive the Thalberg.
And on February 9th, David
Oyelo hosted the Academy's
annual Sci Tech Awards.
Nine scientific and technical achievements
represented by 27
individual award recipients
were honored that night.
And now, please welcome two
time Academy Award winner,
Barbara Streisand.
(applauding)
(cheerful orchestral music)
- Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
When I first saw Black
Klansman, I was stunned.
I was very excited and I was very moved.
It had everything a
great film should have.
It was so real, so funny
and yet so horrifying
because it was based on the truth
and truth is especially
precious these days.
I had to--
(applauding)
Thank you, thank you.
So I had to tweet about it, you know,
about how good it was and
then I got a lovely thank you
from Spike, himself and the
conversation after that,
was very easy because we
were both raised in Brooklyn.
- Oh oh!
(laughing)
- And Spike, we both love hats.
So,
after a lifetime of
bold game changing work,
here is Spike Lee's masterpiece,
the story of the first
African American detective
in the Colorado Springs Police Department
who joins forces with his Jewish colleague
to infiltrate the Ku Klux Klan.
Now that is funny already.
(audience laughing)
But, it's an unflinching look
at race relations in America.
Back in the 1970's, that was then,
but it is just as relevant today.
(applauding)
- This is Ron Stalworth,
I'm anxious to meet you.
- [Man] I'm just happy to be talking with
a true white American.
- They want you to join the Klan?
- They want to meet me first.
- You probably shouldn't
go to that meeting.
- You need to wake up.
Don't think that just because I don't wear
a black beret that I don't
care about my people.
♪ It's too late, it's too late ♪
- [Man] White power!
- [Group] White power!
- You're Jewish, brother,
why you acting like
you ain't got skin in the game?
- That's my business.
- It's our business.
♪ I believe, I believe
I'm falling in love ♪
- [Announcer] Please
welcome last year's winners
for actress in a supporting role
and actor in a leading role,
Allison Janney and Gary Oldman.
(cheerful orchestral music)
(applauding)
- You know, you and I
couldn't have won Oscars
for portraying two more different people.
- That is so true,
one of playing a brash
and controversial leader,
known for loving whiskey and always being
enshrouded in that
trademark cloud of smoke.
- Yes, and then of course
you played Churchill.
(audience laughing)
And here are the nominees for performance
by an actor in a leading role.
Christian Bale, Vice.
- 3000 innocent people burned to death
by those monsters and yet you reject
when I refuse to kiss
those monsters on the cheek
and say pretty please.
You answer me this, what terrorist attack
would you have let go
forward so you wouldn't seem
like a mean and nasty fella?
(applauding)
- [Allison] Bradley
Cooper, A Star Is Born.
- Can I tell you a secret?
I think you might be a song writer.
Don't worry, I won't tell anybody.
But I'm not very good at keeping secrets.
(laughing)
(applauding)
- [Allison] Willem Dafoe,
At Eternity's Gate.
- I believe I have a
menacing spirit around me,
an invisible being.
I feel it, I don't see it.
He speaks to me and threatens me
and all he wants to do is
plunge a knife into my heart.
I saw him and I tried to
cut him out of myself.
(applauding)
- [Allison] Rami Malek, Bohemian Rhapsody.
♪ Come on, oh ♪
♪ I don't want to die ♪
♪ But sometimes we should
never have been born at all ♪
(applauding)
- [Allison] Viggo Mortensen, Green Book.
- You speak German, huh?
- That was Russian.
- Yeah, I was stationed
in Germany in the Army.
I can pick up a little bit
of what you're saying there.
Watch out for them crabs.
They're all snakes.
Kenny should have bombed
them when he had the chance.
(applauding)
- And the Oscar goes to--
- [Together] Rami Malek.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the first Oscar
and nomination for Rami Malek.
(orchestra playing Queen)
- Oh, I, I, oh my god.
My mom is in here somewhere.
Oh, I love you.
I love you, lady.
My family, thank you for all of this.
You know, my dad didn't get
to see me do any of this.
But I think he's looking
down on me right now.
So uh, this is, this
is a monumental moment,
one I'm so appreciative to all of you,
to everyone who has had a
hand in getting me here.
To the Academy, to people
who took a chance on me,
every step of the way.
Graham King, Dennis
O'Sullivan, everyone at Fox
and New Regency, thank you guys so much.
I may not have been the obvious choice,
but I guess it worked out.
(audience laughing)
Thank you, Queen, thank
you guys for being,
for allowing me to be
the tiniest part of your
phenomenal, extraordinary legacy.
I am forever in your debt.
(applauding)
My crew and my cast, I love you.
You are my equals, you are my betters.
I could have never been here without you.
I think about what it would have been like
to tell little bubba Rami that one day
this might happen to him and I think
his curly haired little
mind would be blown.
That kid, he was struggling
with his identity,
trying to figure himself out and
I think to anyone struggling with theirs
and trying to discover their voice,
listen, we made a film about a gay man,
an immigrant who lived his life
just unapologetically himself
and the fact that I'm celebrating him
and this story with you tonight is proof
that we're longing for stories like this.
I am the son of immigrants from Egypt.
I'm a first generation American and--
(applauding)
part of my story is
being written right now
and I could not be more grateful
to each and every one of you and everyone
who believed in me for this moment.
It is something I will treasure
for the rest of my life.
Lucy Boyenton, you're
the heart of this film.
You are beyond immensely talented.
You have captured my heart.
Thank you so much.
(applauding)
(cheerful orchestral music)
- [Announcer] Coming up next,
a look at best picture nominee, Green Book
and the award for best actress.
Will the Oscar go to Yalitza Aparicio,
Glenn Close, Olivia Colman, Lady Gaga,
or Melissa McCarthy?
Keep watching to find out.
- [Woman] If we show emotion,
we're called dramatic.
If we want to play
against men, we're nuts.
And if we dream of equal
opportunity, delusional.
When we stand for
something, we're unhinged.
- [Man] Sue Bird's
gonna need to calm down.
- [Woman] When we're too good,
there's something wrong with us
and if we get angry, we're hysterical
or irrational or just being crazy,
but a woman running a marathon was crazy.
- [Man] Officials tried to
pull her off the course.
- [Woman] A woman boxing was crazy.
A woman dunking, crazy.
Coaching an NBA team, crazy.
A woman competing in a
hijab, changing her story,
landing a double cork 1080,
or winning 23 grand slams, having a baby
and then coming back for more,
crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy and crazy.
So if they wanna call you crazy,
fine, show them what crazy can do.
(energetic orchestral music)
- Today faster than ever
the world is changing
because opportunity is raging,
this reality changing the world we see,
intelligence to build it like
we always hoped it would be,
but it's not really about
what technology can do,
it's about how it's used by you.
In the end it's just a tool so bring it.
What's a hammer without
a person to swing it?
Your possibility is endless.
Your limits are few, so
here's the real question,
what will you do?
- [Announcer] The Oscars will continue
in a moment here on ABC.
- [Man] It's time to go, Toyota,
go connected with a sporty
Camry, with the latest tech,
compatible with your
favorite apps and wi-fi.
Now lease a Camry for $219 a month or buy
with $1500 cash back or go
with a stylish Corolla and
lease for just $199 a month
or buy with $1500 cash back and two years
of no cost maintenance included.
Go, see your Toyota dealer today.
Toyota, let's go places.
- [Man] What is character?
Is is a quality that
forms naturally over time?
Or is it a tree that
grows out of hard work?
Or hardship?
(energetic orchestral music)
The thing about character,
is that while it can be
hard to define, it's
always easy to recognize.
Santa Margherita, for who you are.
- [Man] Do, do your thing.
Flee that nest.
Seize that moment.
Find your inspiration.
Be extraordinary.
Spread your wings and
experience the Mazda CX5
with new signature track and turbo.
Mazda, feel alive.
- [Man] It's a deadly blind
spot right under your nose,
tonight after the Oscars.
- [Announcer] Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome Amanda Stenberg
and congressman, John Lewis.
(cheerful orchestral music)
(applauding)
(cheering)
- Our final nominee for
best picture is a film about
bigotry, friendship and growth,
based on the story of a white man
and an African American man
on a journey through the segregated south.
- I can bear witness that the portrait
of that time and place in
our history is very real.
It is seared in my memory.
Black men and women,
our brothers and sisters
treated as second class citizens,
threatened for raising their family
or earning a living,
beaten and sometimes killed
for the crime of trying to
live a life with dignity.
Our nation battles scars
of that time as do I.
(applauding)
- The characters in Green Book
gradually tore down the walls
between them, transforming
each other in the process.
As this film demonstrates,
any journey that opens someone's eyes
and softens their heart, is
one that is worth taking.
(applauding)
- Young or old,
I encourage you to be an active
participant in a journey.
This is Green Book.
(applauding)
- [Man] Have you ever driven
professionally before?
- I can drive anything.
- What other experience do you have?
- Public relations.
- I'm about to embark on a
concert tour in the deep south.
- You and the deep south,
there's gonna be problems.
Get your hands off him now!
- What are you doing?
- A letter.
- Put this down.
Dear Dolores, the distance between us
is breaking my spirit.
Falling in love with you
was the easiest thing
I have ever done.
- Either I eat in this room
or I'm not performing tonight.
- It takes courage to
change people's hearts.
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Please welcome
Academy Award winners,
Francis McDormant and Sam Rockwell.
(cheerful orchestral music)
- It's an honor for us
to be back on stage.
Francis do you have anything to add?
- No, nope.
Nope, thank you very much.
- Here are the nominees for
performance by an actress
in a leading role.
Yalitza Aparicio, Roma.
(speaking Spanish)
(dogs barking)
(applauding)
- [Francis] Glenn Close, The Wife.
- What we were talking
about the other day.
- Yes.
- I want to say that what
you implied isn't true
and if you malign Joe's talent in any way,
I'll take you to court.
Good luck, Nathaniel, I'm
sure you'll write a fine book.
(applauding)
- [Francis] Olivia Colman, The Favorite.
- They are the ones who've give you some
for quite some time now.
Seemed like the perfect
opportunity with Mulbor winning.
- It is a monstrous extravagance.
Mrs. Morely, we are at war.
- We won.
- Oh, it is not over, we must continue.
- Oh, oh I did not know that.
(applauding)
- [Sam] Lady Gaga, A Star Is Born.
- I want to do this again.
I won't come and find you.
Next time you can clean up your own mess.
(applauding)
- [Sam] Melissa McCarthy,
Can You Ever Forgive Me?
- It wasn't my work, was it,
I mean, if I had put in my work,
and I would have been opening
myself up to criticism
and I'm too much of a coward to do that.
(applauding)
- And the Oscar goes to,
Olivia Coleman.
(cheering)
(applauding)
- [Announcer] This is the first Oscar
and nomination for Olivia Colman.
(cheerful orchestral music)
(audience cheering)
- (crying) Oh, it's
genuinely quite stressful.
(laughing)
This is hilarious.
(stuttering)
Okay, um, I have to thank lots of pe--