- It's only fitting to say
God bless Texas, thanks guys.
- Amen.
- Appreciate it.
(upbeat music)
- Evening everyone, and
welcome to The Next Revolution.
I'm Steve Hilton and this is the home
of the positive populism,
pro-worker, pro-family,
pro-community, and of course
always, but especially
on this July the Fourth
holiday weekend, pro-America.
And that's where we start tonight.
There was a time when being
pro-America was a given
for politicians in both main parties.
Of course President
Reagan put it beautifully
when he talked of a
shining city on a hill.
But I also love Bill Clinton's great line,
"There's nothing wrong with America
"that can't be fixed by
what's right with America."
But this week, this July the fourth,
we saw that those days are gone.
Yes, we still have a
Republican president who,
like Ronald Reagan is
obviously proud of America
and happy to say it, to celebrate it,
but today's Democrats, no,
they're embarrassed by America.
Far from celebrating America,
they want to tear it down
and turn it into something else.
That's the background to President Trump's
Salute to America on Independence Day,
the Democrats couldn't wait to attack it.
- Donald Trump, I believe,
is incapable of celebrating
what makes America great because
I don't think he gets it.
- He doesn't get it, okay look.
Here's some of what the
president actually said.
- Together we are part of one
of the greatest stories ever
told, the story of America.
It is the spirit, daring,
and defiance, excellence,
and adventure, courage, and
confidence, loyalty, and love
that built this country into
the most exceptional nation
in the history of the world.
And our nation is stronger
today than it ever was before.
- I think you'll find Joe
China that President Trump gets
what makes America great than
a knackered old swamp creature
who took billions of dollars in bribes
in the form of payments
to his family businesses
from America's number one enemy.
You are the last person to lecture anyone
on patriotism, hashtag JoeChina.
But it wasn't just him,
it was all of them.
How dare you celebrate
America, cried the left,
it's not who we are.
- It's just not who we are as Americans.
We don't thump our chest,
put tanks in the streets,
fly jets over the Mall
to prove our strength.
- I think reducing our nation
to tanks and shows of muscle
just makes us look like the
kinda loud-mouth guy at the bar.
- I think it's a waste of money.
He's having a parade for himself,
putting tanks out there for himself,
and if he really cares
about the men and women
who are serving our nation,
he'd be investing in higher pay,
better housing, better healthcare.
- By the way, that is exactly
what President Trump has done,
unlike President Obama,
you total charlatan Kirsten Gillibrand.
But the big point is captured
in that smug platitude
trotted out there by the
ridiculous Eric Swalwell,
and the rest of the left these
days, "It's not who we are."
For once that told phrase
told us something useful
about the Democrats this week,
just not the way they intended.
The proud Americans who
stood in the pouring rain
in front of the Lincoln Memorial
to celebrate their country
on July the Fourth know that's
not who the Democrats are.
The millions more who watched at home
and thought finally we have
a president who loves America
as much as we do and isn't
embarrassed to say so,
no that is not who the Democrats are.
The Democrats won't celebrate America
because their new ideology demands
that they denigrate America,
not least with their
reckless, divisive lies
about concentration camps at the border,
collusion with Russia, and
Hitler in the White House.
Today's Democrats are
engaged in a concerted effort
to smear this country at home
and in the eyes of the world.
When they tell you they don't
want to celebrate America
because it's not who we are, believe them.
President Trump, by contrast,
laid out exactly why we should celebrate.
The American spirit he talked
about on Independence Day
has driven some of the most
profound human achievements
in history, from medical
breakthroughs to artistic glories,
to engineering and technological marvels.
American ingenuity has
continually confounded
what the world thinks is possible.
But why, how?
It's not just chance or luck.
There are other countries
with other people
just as talented and ingenious.
Here's my perspective as a recent arrival.
It is America's greatest achievement
that has made all the others possible,
and that is the genius framework
constructed by the founders
and expressed in the founding documents,
all in service of that simple
but revolutionary idea,
liberty under the law.
It's the guarantee of individual liberty
that gave the pioneers the confidence
to set out into the unknown,
that gave the entrepreneurs the belief
they could build something better,
that convinced communities
they could govern themselves.
Power to the people, decentralized
and limited government,
the rule of law, these are the foundation
of the American spirit, and
they have paved the way,
not only for America's
long-lasting democracy,
but also our world-beating economic system
in which investment, innovation,
and above all, success,
are rewarded not punished.
And look at the difference it makes
when we have an
administration that believes
in those American economic values,
another incredible jobs report last week,
incomes rising fastest for those
who are left behind under the Democrats,
record low unemployment,
and a fairer economy.
For example the gap between white
and African American
unemployment has shrunk
by nearly a half since 2016.
The Obama years gave us lower
growth and higher inequality.
With President Trump's
pro-America economics
we have the exact opposite,
higher growth and lower inequality.
But those facts don't
matter to the Democrats.
They've been captured
by an extremist ideology
that is fundamentally anti-American.
You saw it at their
debates the other week,
and it connects everything,
their economic policies,
environmental policies,
healthcare policies,
and yes their hysterical reaction
to President Trump's Salute to America.
Not celebrating America,
but denigrating America.
Now power to the people,
but power for themselves
and the bureaucratic elite.
Not decentralized government,
but everything controlled
from Washington, D.C.
The Democrats don't
want limited government,
they want endless, relentless,
extravagant intervention
by an all-knowing, all-seeing,
all-powerful state.
And here's perhaps the biggest change
from the Democrats of the past.
Today's Democrats don't even
want the most vital element
of the American inheritance,
the rule of law.
At their first presidential debate,
almost all of the 2020 candidates backed
the decriminalization
of illegal immigration.
On Wednesday one of them, Cory Booker,
escorted migrants towards
the US border himself.
Even President Obama's former
Homeland Security Secretary
now says the Democrats are
effectively for open borders.
The Democrats point to
the Statue of Liberty
and say that immigration
control is un-American.
But they forget one vital thing,
it's not just liberty,
it's liberty under the law,
and it is their blatant, thuggish
assault on the rule of law
that is truly un-American.
Let me end on a personal
note about America.
I'm an immigrant here, just
as my parents were in England
after they fled Communism in Hungary.
I've always been pro-immigration,
how could I be anything else?
But it's especially
those of us who believe
in the virtues and benefits of immigration
who should want to see
it properly controlled.
Because public consent
for immigration depends
on government control of immigration.
That's why immigration has
to be done the right way,
according to the rules.
That's certainly how I've
done it since I moved here
with my family seven years ago,
and I thought this July the
Fourth weekend was a good moment
to let you know that I've
now begun the process
of applying for U.S. citizenship.
I can't tell you how much I
appreciate the opportunities
this country has given me,
and the welcome you've all shown me.
And now I'm looking forward one day
to celebrating Independence
Day as an American,
if you'll have me, that is.
Let me know, @SteveHiltonX,
and @NextRevFNC.
Here now, our guests for the night,
Trump 2020 Campaign Senior
Advisor, Katrina Pierson,
and Fox News Contributor,
former Utah Congressman,
and author of the new book
"Power Grab" Jason Chaffetz.
All right, lots of topics
in there, immigration,
the Democrats going nuts.
Where do you wanna start?
- Well I think I'll start by saying
of course we welcome you.
- That's a relief, thank you.
- I applaud you
on your efforts there.
We need more Americans that
fight like you for this country.
But you know I think you
have it exactly right.
They're not even hiding it anymore, Steve.
The Democrats are anti-American.
And we see it, and we've seen
it for the last few years.
They didn't even have a
flag, during the debate
that you mentioned that they
had last week, on stage.
They've been fighting the
flag for the last few years.
They're anti-American, period.
50% of Americans are deplorables,
and the other 50% are just as expendable
because their main focus and priority
are on the families and
children of illegal aliens
and foreign nationals on the way.
So I think you're absolutely right.
I think most Americans see that.
And there were Democrats at
that event in Washington, D.C.,
who watched this president
and who were excited
to be there because there
are some Democrats left
in this country who love
it, and who support it,
because it is the United
States of America.
It is the best country in the world.
It is exactly why everyone
is trying to come here.
- [Steve] Yes that's right,
and I'm one of them, exactly.
- And it's so upsetting
when you show clips that you showed,
what these Democrats were saying.
Frankly in my opinion,
any presidential candidate
that is criticizing saluting
America on Independence Day
should be disqualified.
- I think, well said, I mean look, Jason,
the Democrats would say that's outrageous,
we're not anti-American,
we just have a different set of ideas
about how to bring about
change and everything.
But when you actually look at
the way they're running around
deliberately distorting
and making stuff up
to make America look bad,
and then when you look at the fundamentals
of their shift to the left,
it contradicts something very important
about the kind of spirit
and soul of this country.
- The president believes
in American exceptionalism.
I believe in it, and yet
Democrats are almost embarrassed
about the country, they're
embarrassed about the flag,
they're embarrassed that this president
has wrapped himself in the
flag, I mean literally.
Remember that scene where he came out
and he hugged the flag?
But I think that's why
the overwhelming majority
of Americans love this president,
because it's the one thing
that's supposed to draw us together,
is the flag of the
United States of America.
It shouldn't be a partisan issue,
but the Democrats are choosing
to make it a partisan issue,
and I think they do so at
their own political peril.
And I really like the
sum of what you're saying
in your opening statement,
which I absolutely loved,
which is this idea that the rule of law
does give us the liberty,
and we do believe in limited government,
and there is a fundamental difference
between what the Democrats believe in,
which is more, bigger government,
and what President Trump is fighting for
which is to increase our liberties
by giving the American
people more chances,
more opportunities, and
a better economy in which
to thrive economically.
- Yeah, because in the past,
I think, you could say
that political debate
over policy areas was within a framework
that was recognizably American,
and different from
anywhere else in the world.
It was really interesting
to me when President Trump
had that great line in
his speech to Congress,
"This will never be a socialist country."
Anywhere else in the world,
that would have been a
really weird thing to say.
People would have said well
maybe it will, maybe it won't,
we'll see what happens in the election,
but actually, everyone just
thought that makes sense here
because there's something
about the way socialism
demands this total centralized government
that just is fundamentally anti-American.
- Well it is, and the people
in this country won't allow it,
regardless of how things
proceed down the line.
But to Jason's point, they
were all about big government,
but it's not about big government.
It is about power, they
just don't say that.
In order to have all of the power,
they have to have the
government as big as possible
so that they can control everyone,
they'll exempt themselves,
just like they've always done in the past.
But it is about power and
this erratic derangement
that we see among the
Democrats and in the media,
although I repeat myself, is really coming
from this trauma of the
November 2016 election.
And they grasp onto this toxicity,
and that's why you see
them constantly attacking
innocent people as deplorable,
and you see them attacking
inanimate objects
because now they're unhinged because,
and we know this to be true,
because you saw this debate.
You had this plethora of
Democrat candidates out there
who were saying outrageous things
with ridiculously stupid policies,
and then what do we have today?
President Trump's approval is
now the highest it's ever been
and that gives you a clue
on where Americans stand
on these issues today.
- Well we're gonna look, I'm
sorry, out of time Jason,
but we're gonna look at the
policy shift to the left
a bit later in the show.
And I just want to add as well
as the deb-roar-ah's thing
was so deeply revealing of where they are,
and even though they're gonna say
oh we mustn't make that mistake again,
and they say oh we must understand
the heartland, and so on,
you know they way they talk and act
they really look down their
nose from a cultural perspective
- Yep.
- Absolutely.
- at America, even the food they eat,
and that's why they
can't stand Donald Trump
because he kinda connects
with that and represents that
and gives voice to that.
All right, before we take a break
I have to mention the
U.S. women's soccer team
winning the World Cup earlier today.
What a great way to close
out July the Fourth weekend,
many, many congratulations
to the whole squad
for a fantastic and inspiring achievement.
After the break,
the people versus Chief
Justice John Roberts.
Yes, it's gonna be a
controversial one, don't go away.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Thanks Golden Corral.
Dan gets a slow-smoked sirloin,
and my little trio are as
happy as shrimp, oops clams.
And Mom got it all,
hook, line, and sirloin.
The slow-smoked sirloin and shrimp trio.
Golden Corral, the only one
- [Group In Unison] For everyone.
- Dear OxiClean, I live on a farm
with my hard-working
husband, two active kids,
lots of horses, and two
dogs, which means I always
have a pile of dirty laundry,
sweaty, stinky laundry.
So when I discovered
OxiClean with odor blasters
I was excited to give it a try.
I just add a scoop to my
laundry, and guess what.
There was no odor, it was gone.
Thanks OxiClean for making
life a lot less smelly.
- OxiClean with odor blasters
eliminates tough odors.
- Fact is every insurance
company hopes you drive safely.
But Allstate actually helps you
drive safely with Drivewise.
It lets you know when you go too fast
(squeaking)
and brake too hard,
(brakes squeal)
with feedback to help you drive safer,
giving you the power to
actually lower your cost.
Unfortunately
(rumbling and squealing)
it can't do anything about that.
Now that you know the truth
(horn honking)
are you in good hands?
- [Narrator] It's time for our
lowest prices of the season
on the Sleep Number 360 Smart Bed.
It senses your movement
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
The queen Sleep Number
360 C4 Smart Bed now 1299,
plus free premium delivery when
you add a base, ends Sunday.
- You've got three minutes
to prove how funny you are.
But if you do it, your
life is about to change.
- I get too attached too easily,
I think that's why I can't go to prison.
It's not so much the
showers I'm afraid of,
it's just like what if I fall in love,
you know what I mean?
(audience laughs)
♪ It's real funny ♪
- Kenan with his run on
SNL, Jeff with standup,
I get to be the voice of the people.
- What happens in Vegas,
stays in Vegas, no it don't.
What happens in Vegas
turned five in February.
(audience laughs)
- [Man] It's one of the wildest
comedy clubs I've ever seen.
(audience cheers and applauds)
- [Narrator] Bring the
Funny, premieres after AGT,
check your local listings.
- [Announcer] The
Kavanaugh hearings exposed,
new insight into the confirmation
that captivated America,
get can't miss insight
from the authors of "Justice on Trial,"
Monday on The Story.
- Frank!
- Frank, over here!
(shutters click)
- Frank, Frank.
So Frank, you the Big Hurt,
why do you need Nugenix?
- After 40, a guy loses
free testosterone, even me.
I couldn't stay in shape like I used to.
- Frank!
- So does Nugenix really work?
- Yes, it's the number one selling
free testosterone booster at GNC.
- Okay great, but does it work for you?
- [Frank] Oh yeah, my
workouts are incredible now.
I'm feeling stronger, more
energetic, with a lot more drive.
(reporters shout over each other)
- So say I knew someone
who should try Nugenix.
How does he do that?
- It's easy, just send a text
to get a complimentary bottle.
- [Narrator] Frank's
right, now you can claim
a complimentary bottle
of award-winning Nugenix
by texting ELITE to 369369.
Its unique man-boosting
formula is powered by Testofen,
a patented key ingredient
clinically researched
to help a man feel stronger, leaner,
more energetic, and more passionate.
- And trust me, you'll
like the difference too.
- [Narrator] Samples are
not available in stores,
so text E-L-I-T-E to 369369
for a complimentary bottle of Nugenix.
(upbeat music)
- This week the Trump
administration announced
that it still intends to
put a citizenship question
on the 2020 census, despite
an unfavorable ruling
in the Supreme Court the previous week
which temporarily blocked the plan.
But whatever the arguments
about the census question,
there was an aspect of the ruling,
and especially the majority
opinion from the Chief Justice,
that will have long-lasting
and disastrous consequences
for the country way beyond the census.
And so tonight,
it's the people versus
Chief Justice John Roberts.
The argument used by the Chief Justice
to block the citizenship
question was that the rationale
for the change given by
Commerce Secretary Wilbur Ross
is that he was responding to a request
from the Justice Department
wasn't the real reason.
Documents showed that he was planning
to put the citizenship
question on the census
before the Justice
Department request came in.
But so what, under the Constitution,
it's an executive branch
decision that has long been
a legal precedent in this country
that the courts can't object
to executive branch actions
just because there are other reasons
for the decision than those stated.
John Roberts has just
overturned that precedent,
and this will have massive and
deeply damaging implications
for the way things work, or
rather don't work, in America.
In the dissent of the case,
written by Justice Clarence Thomas,
and joined by Justices Gorsuch
and Kavanaugh, he wrote,
"The court has opened a Pandora's Box
"of pretext-based challenges
in administrative law."
All right, so what does all
this mean in plain English,
and what does it mean for you?
How many times have you been
frustrated that something
this administration wants
to do has been overruled,
overturned, struck down, slowed down,
or watered down by the courts?
You voted to build the wall,
but the courts said no.
You voted to defund sanctuary cities,
On DACA, on asylum, on healthcare,
on rolling back some regulations,
even on blocking immigration
from failed states
with high levels of terrorism,
the courts said no to
policies that you voted for.
All in all, unelected judges have ruled
against the Trump administration
more than 70 times
in the last three years,
way more than the rate for
previous administrations.
This is what happens when you vote
for a populist revolution.
The establishment tries to overturn it
through undemocratic means.
And now this ruling from
Chief Justice Roberts
will make it all 10 times worse.
From now on, any partisan pressure group
will be able to take legal
action against the administration
on all sorts of spurious grounds,
helping, as Justice Thomas says, quote,
"partisans to use the courts
to harangue executive officers
"through depositions, discovery,
delay, and distraction."
Great, that's just what we need,
an even more politicized judiciary,
even more roadblocks in the way
of actually getting things
done that help your life.
The worst of it all is
John Roberts own rationale
for this, his own motive,
for him it is all about
the image of the Court.
Now that he's the swing vote,
he doesn't want to make
his court look partisan.
So the other week he balanced
his ruling on gerrymandering
with this damaging one
on judicial review of executive decisions.
But he's supposed to be the Chief Justice,
not the chief PR.
He's supposed to interpret
the Constitution,
not what the media will
say about his court.
This ruling will hurt
America for years to come.
It should haunt Chief Justice Roberts
for the rest of his time on the bench.
But above all, it shows the importance
of taking his power away
by reelecting Donald Trump
so he can put Roberts in the
minority where he belongs.
Okay, tell me what you think of that,
@SteveHiltonX and @NextRevFNC.
Jason Chaffetz.
- No, well said.
I think this is one of the worst decisions
and put on a list of bad
decisions from Justice Roberts.
I think Clarence Thomas had it right.
You don't want these judges
making subjective rulings
from the bench based on
whatever political whims that they want.
Inherently the legislative
branch is political,
and it will change from time
to time, but that's okay.
You shouldn't have to state the reason
and try to get into the mind
and try to be the mind reader
of what they were really looking for,
especially in this case of the census
where they have precedent
in order to do it.
So I know we're gonna
talk more about that,
but really this is a bad decision.
They can't let the courts
just try to be mind readers,
and then subject their
own will upon the court.
That's not what they're supposed to do.
- Yeah, I mean the thing is Katrina,
some people have made the
comparison with his decision
on Obamacare back in 2012, wasn't it,
where he basically voted
to let most of it stand.
And the real reason people speculated was
that he didn't want to look
as if he was killing off
something that was just
a political priority
for the then-president.
But now, for the same kind of reason,
to sort of oh it's all about
image, he's done something
that actually wasn't just a
one off thing like Obamacare,
this will hurt so many
different areas of policy,
and stop, people are so
frustrated, government,
nothing ever happens,
this is all just talk
and nothing gets done, this is why.
- Well it is why, and it seems
like Chief Justice Roberts
wants his legacy to be
generational destruction.
It was far worse back with Obamacare
because it was unconstitutional
and at that point in time
you had Justice Roberts
literally bent over backwards,
trying to reform the
individual mandate into a tax,
therefore it would be good to go,
something that our Congress,
the people who actually
represent the people,
didn't even vote on.
There was no tax that was
voted on with Obamacare,
but oh this is fine, let's just
push this right on through.
And that has been
destructive for generations,
as we've seen, and now here
we are with something that,
to Jason's point, it's not unprecedented.
This was a question that was
on the census before in history
so it's not brand new,
it's not like the president
seizing power of anything,
and the intent by someone
who recommended it,
now all of the sudden is directing
the Supreme Court of the United States?
This is insanity?
- That's what drives me crazy.
I've worked inside of a government,
you've obviously been in Con,
there's so many factors, and
conversations, and meetings,
and discussions, and memos, all of that,
now can be got hold of by
any kind of legal challenge
of any kind of political
decision, it's a total nightmare.
- And there are those
of us that are worried
that when it goes to the courts,
they can make that sorta
subjective analysis
and say well this one's right
and this one's not right.
That's not what they're supposed to do.
The court is supposed
to rule whether or not
they can add a question or
not, it should be that simple.
But they've opened up this box because,
I think you're exactly right Steve,
it's not just this case.
It is going to live on in perpetuity,
and it will create all kinds of problems.
It will empower the court more
to make subjective decisions.
- And court all the way down,
this is not just,
- Yes.
- You have the state
level, it just opens up
this possibility that you
try and get anything done,
I mean we already know how bad it is,
it's just gonna get worse.
And people are gonna
get more disillusioned
with politics and government
because it's gonna get
even more impossible to do anything.
- Well we've always said
that it's President Trump
against the world, and every
day we see that to be true,
more and more over time.
But hopefully the president
will be able to move forward
on this either through executive action
or some other manner, to again force this
through the court system.
It is common sense,
a country has a right to know who's in it.
This is not some weird twisted thing
that they're trying to make it out to be.
This is a power grab, this is what it is.
The Democrats want as many
people in this country
as possible because the numbers,
aside from whether or
not they're citizens,
gives them the electoral advantage
when it comes to
distribution of Congressman,
and they want more of that.
It is all about a power grab,
that's what it's always been.
They don't care about people,
they don't care about race,
they don't care about gender,
they just want the people on their side.
- Well there you are, so that,
as you mentioned, we're
gonna be talking more
about that aspect of it,
that was the sort of central ruling.
I wanted to make sure everyone understood
the wider implications of the ruling,
but specific on the census question,
we're gonna be talking about
that on tomorrow's Deep Dive
on Fox Nation, go to
foxnation.com and sign up
if you haven't done that already,
gonna be a great discussion.
All right, coming up, Senator Josh Hawley
on the dangers of China
getting their hands
on sensitive American technology
and the law he introduced to stop it.
(upbeat music)
(exclaims)
(laughter)
- I'm looking at that truck.
- Wow.
- That's awesome!
- [Narrator] This Fourth of July,
celebrate in a new Chevrolet.
- [Man] Oh wow.
- They're all really cool cars.
- [Woman] Ooh, I love it.
- I like those lights.
- Look how beautiful this is.
- This is amazing.
- I can't stop staring at it.
- [Narrator] Spectacular
deals are on display now
at your local Chevy dealer.
- Wow!
- Do you love it?
- [Man] It's time to upgrade.
- [Narrator] Now during the
Fourth of July Sales Event,
current GM owners can get
over $5600 below MSRP on this Equinox.
The Fourth of July Sales
Event ends July 8th.
- Let's be honest, you don't really talk
about your insurance unless
you're complaining about it.
You go on about how.
- It's so confusing, it hurts my brain.
- Yeah, I hear ya.
- Or you say you can't believe.
- How much of a hassle it is.
- And tell anyone who'll listen.
(woman speaks gibberish)
She said it's so expensive.
- Tell me about it.
- Yes, I'm telling the people at home.
That's why Esurance is
making the whole experience
surprisingly painless so you
never have to talk about it,
unless you're the spokesperson.
Esurance, it's surprisingly painless.
- Introducing the DPR Pulse,
the world's first battery-powered
trimmer on wheels.
Pop in the 62 volt power pack
and you're ready to roll.
Trim along gardens, stone
walls, and fence lines.
Mow down waist-high weeds.
The DR Pulse is the easiest
to use trimmer/mower ever.
Check out the full line of DRs today.
- [Narrator] For your free
buyer's guide and DVD,
call 1-800-510-1989, free shipping is now
in effect online at DRtrimmer.com
- [Announcer] Jimmy's gotten
used to his whole room
smelling like sweaty odors,
yep he's gone nose blind.
(alarm blares)
He thinks it smells fine,
but his mom smells this.
(ding)
Luckily for all your hard-to-wash fabrics,
there's Febreze Fabric Refresher.
Febreze doesn't just
mask, it eliminates odors
you've gone nose blind to.
And try Febreze Unstoppables for fabric,
with up to twice the fresh scent power,
you'll wanna try it again, and again,
and maybe just one more time.
Indulge in irresistible freshness,
Febreze Unstoppables, breathe happy.
- Ride along with the real heroes.
(dramatic music)
(beeping)
Every call, every emergency
is a life on the line.
(siren blaring)
- [Narrator] First Responders Live,
Wednesdays or anytime on FOX NOW or Hulu.
(rhythmic drumming and clapping)
- [Narrator] Save up to
65%, call 1-800-BEACHES.
- I love Rakuten, it's
basically free money.
- [Woman] It's an easy
way to earn cash back
on the stuff I'm already buying.
- When you have a child and
they're constantly growing
out of clothing, earning
cash back from Rakuten
just makes everything easier.
- It's not just 3%, sometimes it's 8%,
but you're always getting cash back.
- The way cash back works on Rakuten
is so they get a commission from the store
and then they share
that commission with me.
- And you have money, more
money to spend because you got
- [Both Women] Free money.
- [Narrator] Go to
rakuten.com and sign up today
for a $10 bonus.
- [Announcer] Fox News
channel on SiriusXM,
your favorite shows on channel 114,
plus every story, every 15 minutes,
Fox News Headlines 24/7 channel 115.
(upbeat music)
- Welcome back everyone.
Last week I had the chance to talk
to Missouri Senator Josh Hawley
about his positive and practical plan
to protect the U.S. from the
China threat, take a look.
One of the members of
Congress who has been toughest
on the threat from China
is Senator Josh Hawley
from Missouri, he joins us now.
Senator, I've been watching
what you've been doing
and saying on China with great approval,
I'm very excited to talk to you about it.
First of all, big picture,
how would you set out for
us the threat from China?
- The threat from China is
the most significant threat
of the 21st century in many ways.
I mean they've already
taken our jobs, Steve.
They're trying to steal our technology.
They're trying to build their military
on the back of our middle class.
And it's time that we
got tough with China,
I mean we can't continue to allow them
to run roughshod over us.
That means getting tough
with them on trade.
It means getting tough with
them on stealing our technology
and stealing our jobs.
- One specific aspect I think
that you've rightly focused on
is the connection between
our technology companies
and the Chinese military,
and you've got a specific
proposal on that,
tell us about that.
- My proposal is this,
that Chinese researchers
who want to come over to the United States
should have to, and work
on sensitive technologies
in our labs, should have to go
through background screening
to make sure that they're
not actually agents
of the Chinese government
or the Chinese military.
It's just an additional layer
of security to make sure that,
again, China is not using
their researchers to be spies.
And unfortunately we know that
China has tried to do this,
and by the way so has
Russia, and so has Iran.
So my bill would put a stop to that.
It would say that you've gotta go
through this extra background check
if you wanna work on sensitive
technology in American labs.
- What about the way in
which China over the years
has really kind of burrowed
into our establishment,
not just academia and
the scientific world,
as you've just described,
the technology world,
but honestly when you look at Washington
and the Chinese influence through
think tanks, and lobbying,
and so on, there's one
particularly egregious example
that we've highlighted on this show,
which is President Obama's
former Head of Cybersecurity,
now working for Jones Day, a
law firm in Washington, D.C.,
as a declared lobbyist for
Huawei, which our government
has designated a national security threat.
Don't you think that whole practice
of lobbying for a foreign government
that is basically a strategic
threat to this country
should not just be declared,
as it has been in this
case, but actually outlawed?
- I would say that that's
very, very concerning, Steve,
and you are absolutely right
that the Chinese government,
the Chinese military has
worked to gain access
to our universities, to think tanks.
They have worked to weaponize
in many ways our free system,
whether it's our open trade system,
which they have cheated at
systematically for years,
or whether it's trying
to conduct espionage
on our own college campuses,
or whether it's forcing American companies
who want to do business in China
to sign these technology
transfer agreements
whereby they take all of our tech and then
ultimately don't give us
access to the market anyway.
So it is time that we realized
the threat that China poses
to our middle class, to
our safety and security,
and got serious about it.
- Would you go so far
as to say that there's
a comparison here with the
Cold War and the Soviet Union?
A lot of people are
talking in those terms.
And that actually we
should really be looking
at some kind of systematic disengagement,
or at least reducing
our dependence on China,
because we would never have made ourselves
so economically, and technologically,
and in other ways dependent
on the Soviet Union, would we?
- I think we absolutely need to make sure
we are not dependent on China.
And we need to recognize
them for what they are,
which is at best a strategic competitor,
probably an adversary.
I mean just look right now
Steve at how they're trying
to hold hostage farmers, for
instance, farmers in my state,
making them the focus of
retaliation on these tariffs.
That's the kind of game
China plays, they cheat,
and then when you try to
hold them accountable,
they strike back, they
try to inflict pain.
We've got to put ourselves in a position
to compete with them, to win,
and to protect our people.
- All right, last question.
So we've been really focusing
on one particular individual
and his connections to China,
that's former vice president Joe Biden.
We've been telling our
audience week after week
how he is compromised by China,
while he was vice president,
billions of dollars
from the Chinese state to
Biden family businesses.
It seems to me extraordinary
that there's no real interest
in following this up, other than here
and a few other places on this channel.
What do you think we should,
don't you think that this
should be properly investigated?
Joe China as I like to call
him should be investigated.
- Absolutely, I think we
need to follow the evidence
to where it leads, and you can
see in Joe Biden's comments
about China saying that
they're not really a threat,
saying that they really
aren't a competitor,
that we don't have
anything to worry about.
I mean, Steve, the best thing
you can say about that is
is that it's just totally ignorant,
I mean it is willful ignorance.
China is a huge threat to us,
and they have been for years.
Look at the jobs that they have
taken from American workers,
from workers in my home state of Missouri,
and that's the tip of the iceberg.
They wanna be a global
superpower at our expense.
We cannot let them.
- All right, well I'm
really pleased to see
that you recognize this
threat for what it is
and you're there fighting
on behalf of our national interest.
Great to see you this
evening, thank you Senator.
- Thank you.
- Coming up, a Swamp Watch update.
Billionaire pedophile Jeffrey Epstein
was arrested by the Feds last night.
But what about some accountability
from the man who gave
him a sweetheart deal?
The details are next.
(upbeat music)
(phones ring)
- Uh oh, looks like
someone's still nervous
about buying a new house.
- Is it that obvious?
- Yes it is, you know
maybe you'd worry less
if you got Geico to help with
your homeowner's insurance.
- I didn't know Geico helps
with homeowner's insurance.
- Yeah, they've been doin' it for years.
What are you doing?
Hey Steve?
- Thanks man.
- There he is.
- [Announcer] Get to know
Geico and see how much
you could save on homeowner's
and renter's insurance.
- [Narrator] Every year it
all starts in the same place.
(grunts)
- Right there, right there.
- [Narrator] Training camp.
- Get something out of the drill,
everything we do is for a reason.
- [Narrator] And NFL
Network has nine hours
of coverage every day.
- [Man] Do the little things right,
and the big things will
take care of themselves.
- [Narrator] With access to all 32 teams.
- Nice job, that a way!
- [Narrator] It's time to go to work.
Inside Training Camp Live
starts July 22nd on NFL Network.
- [Woman] Dear Oxiclean, I live on a farm
with my hard-working
husband, two active kids,
and lots of horses, so I use
OxiClean with odor blasters.
Just one scoop and odor's
gone, thanks OxiClean.
- OxiClean with odor blasters
eliminates tough odors.
(applause)
- Priceline will partner
with even more Vegas hotels
to turn their unsold
rooms into amazing deals.
Delegates, how do you vote?
(screaming)
♪ Yeah, yes, yes ♪
- [Woman] That is freaky.
Priceline, every trip is a big deal.
- [Narrator] With moderate
to severe ulcerative colitis
or Crohn's your plans
can change in minutes.
Your head wants to do one thing,
but your gut says not today.
If your current treatment isn't working,
ask your doctor about Entyvio.
Entyvio acts specifically in the GI tract
to prevent an excess of white blood cells
from entering and causing
damaging inflammation.
Entyvio has helped many patients
achieve long-term relief and remission.
Infusion and serious
allergic reactions can happen
during or after treatment.
Entyvio may increase risk of infection,
which can be serious.
PML, a rare, serious,
potentially fatal brain infection
caused by a virus may be possible.
Tell your doctor if you have an infection,
experience frequent infections,
or have flu-like symptoms or sores.
Liver problems can occur with Entyvio.
Ask your doctor about the
only GI-focused biologic,
just for ulcerative colitis and Crohn's.
Entyvio, relief and
remission within reach.
- I didn't really know anything
about my family history.
Went to Ancestry, I put in the names
of my grandparents first,
I got a leaf right away.
A leaf is a hint that is connected
to each person in your family tree.
I learned that my 10
times great grandmother
is George Washington's aunt.
Within a few days, I went
from knowing almost nothing
to holy crow I'm related
to George Washington.
This is my cousin George.
- [Narrator] Discover your story.
Start searching for free
now at ancestry.com.
(country music)
(frogs croak)
- Remember Jeffrey Epstein,
the hedge fund billionaire
who ran a repulsive
under-age sex pyramid scheme
and was handed a cushy plea deal
by Labor Secretary Alexander Acosta
who was then Florida U.S. Attorney,
amounting to 13 months in
county jail with work release?
In a Swamp Watch last December,
I called for Acosta's
resignation for his role
in this horrific abuse of justice.
You helped cover up a
billionaire's pedophile sex crimes
on an epic scale.
Now you're in President Trump's cabinet,
and I think you owe all of us
an explanation and an apology.
And if you can't do that,
it's time for you to go.
Well the skeleton in
Acosta's closet is back
in the public eye following
Epstein's arrest this weekend
on charges of sex trafficking.
So will we finally see some
accountability from Alex Acosta?
In my view, it really
is time for him to go.
Look, I think what drives people crazy,
in this case and in so
many others, Katrina,
is this sense that people
just do things in their past,
life moves on, it's the swamp,
there's no accountability,
no one's actually held responsible
for things that they did.
- Well look, I think,
specifically for this case,
you literally have to go back to 2002
to really grasp the bizarre circumstances
that have surrounded this
case and the people around it.
And it is quite disturbing when you look
at all of the allegations,
dozens of women, young girls,
which I have a zero tolerance policy for,
and I think at this point,
if you are the story, that's a problem.
And I think that's where we are today,
given the new arrest,
and we'll know tomorrow
when we see what the actual charges are,
if these indeed are new.
There are reports that
these are new charges,
new allegations from recent people.
And if that turns out to
be true, then we probably
should look at making
some significant changes,
if this turns out to be
what it's said to be.
- [Steve] What do you make of it?
- I think the Chief of Staff,
the acting Chief of Staff Mick Mulvaney,
has probably had some serious discussions
with the Labor Secretary.
Serving in the president's
cabinet is a privilege,
it is not a right.
Every time I've seen
Donald Trump in action,
when there has been a flare up,
and there has been something
where somebody has gone over the line,
the president has taken care of this.
I would be surprised in this case
if the president allowed
it to continue and fester.
He's taking some op eds
and some serious concern
from people that are big
fans of the president.
I don't see why this person,
or how this person can continue on.
And I think you were ahead of your time
by calling it out in December,
and it's exacerbated
by what's going on now.
- We should be clear, it's
not anything he's done
since President Trump
appointed him, this is,
as you said, long time ago.
But there's something about
it, it's so egregious,
it's so revolting, you just think come on.
- Well there, you have to deal with it.
And when you continue to
make yourself the issue
and distract from the president's agenda,
you no longer need to be serving there.
And this is not going to go away,
this case is gonna continue on.
And the coziness and the relationship,
I think the more people
look at how this guy,
the Labor Secretary,
dealt with it back then
is really bad stuff.
- Well you know the argument
they're making is that
even through his confirmation hearing,
there were U.S. Attorney Generals who,
U.S. Attorneys who looked at this
over three different administrations,
so there was something maybe we don't know
that was going on at that point in time,
and the government does
what the government does,
and we don't always know why.
But I do think that now, if true,
that these allegations are new and recent,
then all of those things
are gonna be opened.
And at that point, either
he should say something,
or step aside so this can play out.
- And remember, the Labor
Secretary is the one
that's supposed to
oversee human trafficking.
So it just gets even
worse because of the fact
that that's his job,
is supposed to be overseeing
human trafficking,
and his record on human trafficking,
just based on this one
case alone, is horrific.
- Just to sort of wrap that up,
this guy Epstein, you know
the real villain of the peace,
for years it seems he's
gotten away with it,
and looks like finally
now in this administration
he might be getting the
justice he deserves.
All right, coming up,
after this past week,
it's clear the loonies have
taken over the Democrat party,
Loony Left is next.
(upbeat music)
- Last year the internet told
IHOP to stick to pancakes.
Well here they are,
(audience cheers)
pancakes with all
natural Black Angus beef.
Isn't that right, Mister Pancake?
- [Sing Song Voice] It's a pancake.
- But that's a bur.
- [Narrator] Try one
starting at 6.99, IHOP.
- Do you ever wish you weren't a mo-tore?
- No.
(Western music)
- [Announcer] For those who were born
to ride, there's Progressive.
- [Narrator] Occasional bladder leakage?
- I've had it.
- [Narrator] Had it with bladder leakage?
Azo Bladder Control does
what liners and pads can't,
it supports bladder muscle strength
to help reduce leakage.
(playful music)
- [Announcer] Booking.com
offers free cancellations,
so bookers can book now
(clicks, buzzes)
(bell dings)
and ask their boss later.
- Do you want breakfast?
- [Announcer] Free cancellations
- Definitely breakfast.
- How good is that?
Be a booker at booking.com.
(jazzy music)
- [Narrator] Sean is back,
taking you inside the biggest headlines
and covering the hot button issues
with an all-star lineup you
can't miss, Monday on Hannity.
(glass clinks as it shatters)
(birds chirp)
- [Boy] Nice going, Spencer.
- I can't believe we broke
Old Man Hennessy's window.
- Correction dude, you
broke, I just threw the ball.
- This is really bad.
What are we gonna do?
- [Boys In Unison] We?
- [Boy] Go to the door,
ask for the ball back.
- [Boy] Are you serious?
- It's my ball Myrtlebeck.
- I am so dead.
- I'd run away.
- Yeah, to Uruguay.
- Kiss your life goodbye, sorry.
- [Boy] Let's go.
("That's What Friends Are
For" by Bacharach and Sager)
- [Boy] See ya, remember me
in your will.
- Hope ya had a nice life.
- [Boy] Some friends you are!
♪ Keep smiling, keep shining ♪
- Hi.
♪ Knowing you can always count on me ♪
- Tell him it was an accident
and we can fix the window.
♪ For sure ♪
Come on.
I'll come with you.
♪ That's what friends are for ♪
- [Narrator] Loyalty, pass it on.
- [Girl] You go first.
- [Narrator] A message from
the Foundation for a Better Life.
- Frank!
- Frank, over here!
(shutters click)
- Frank, Frank!
So Frank, you're the Big Hurt.
Why do you need Nugenix?
- After 40, a guy loses
free testosterone, even me.
I couldn't stay in shape like I used to.
- Frank!
- So does Nugenix really work?
- Yes, it's the number one selling
free testosterone booster at GNC.
- Okay great, but does it work for you?
- Oh yeah, my workouts are incredible now.
I'm feeling stronger, more
energetic, with a lot more drive.
(reporters shout over each other)
- So say I knew someone
who should try Nugenix.
How does he do that?
- It's easy, just send a text
to get a complimentary bottle.
- [Announcer] Frank's
right, now you can claim
a complimentary bottle
of award-winning Nugenix
by texting NEW to 321321.
Its unique man-boosting
formula is powered by Testofen,
a patented key ingredient
clinically researched
to help a man feel stronger, leaner,
more energetic, and more passionate.
- And trust me, you'll
like the difference too.
- [Announcer] Samples are
not available in stores,
so text N-E-W to 321321
for a complimentary bottle of Nugenix.
(upbeat music)
- This is not 2016, this is
2020, and people are woke.
- You can say that again.
The entire Democratic party
is this week's Loony Left.
(mysterious music)
When Kamala Harris
says, "People are woke,"
she seems to be talking
about her fellow candidates.
The mainstream Democrat positions now look
like they are open borders,
free healthcare for illegal immigrants,
abolition of private healthcare
for American citizens,
His-pandering, trans-pandering,
woke-pandering.
Yes, it's official, the Loony
Left is no longer the fringe,
it has taken over the Democratic Party.
- I mean look, I mean
this is just laughable.
I mean when you see
someone like Kamala Harris
pandering to black people,
you know there's a problem.
And look, there is
actually a nickname for her
with my black friends and online,
you see actual African Americans
that call her Chameleon Harris
because she is pandering.
And the only people that are woke now
because of her candidacy
are the black people
who are actually descendants from slaves
because there's been this whole uproar
because she's presenting herself,
and the media's presenting
herself as African American.
She's an Islander American and
she should be proud of that.
But that's not what's happening.
She's given in to what you just discussed,
all of the His-pandering,
the trans-pandering,
and now she's trying to really beef up
her African American credential by using,
I guess, I don't know, woke.
- I mean it's just ridiculous.
I know he misspoke and has cleaned it up,
but for example Julian Castro going on
about abortions for trans women,
it's just one example,
just the endless pandering.
- Reproductive justice.
- And then you've got the policy shifts,
where they all put their
hand up for these positions
that are so extreme, compared
to just a couple of years ago.
- Well and just recently the
Democrats have just shown
that they have a distaste
and they don't like the flag,
they don't like the Fourth
of July celebration,
they're embarrassed by anybody who wants
to stand up and wrap
themselves in the flag,
and they put themselves
in a terrible position.
But I think that's when
your focus is on pandering
and just winning, as opposed
to having a principle,
and staking that principle in the ground.
When you're rudder-less,
this is what happens,
you start meandering wherever
the news of the day goes,
and the next thing you know you're left
with appeasing a very, very
small percentage of Americans,
and you're leaving 80% of the country,
who loves the country, behind.
- And what are they think this is,
I mean do they think they can
just kind of change all this
when it comes to the general election,
once they've finished
with their pandering,
and whoever the nominee is gets elected,
they can just sort of
ditch all this, or what?
- Well I mean that's the plan,
the plan is to win the primary.
And you have the furthest of the left,
the ones that are actually
falling of the cliff,
these are the people that the
Democrats are pandering to
with all of the isms that are out there.
As ridiculous as it sounds,
they do believe this is
some sort of strategy
because what we've seen is I don't think
they have any intention
on moving to the center,
even after the general election because
they're not going to move.
- That's the interesting
question is this is,
as you might say it's worse
than that, they really mean it.
- They mean it.
(laughing)
- Exactly, and this Trump
derangement syndrome,
I think is very real.
- It's very real.
- Because if Donald Trump likes the flag,
they don't like it.
If he is wanting to protect the border,
then they want open borders.
It doesn't mean,
doesn't seem to matter.
- It's interesting though,
I wanna focus on the open borders thing
because that one really
interests me particularly,
because they hate that label.
They always say, "We're
not for open borders,"
but it's fascinating to see,
over the last couple of weeks,
since that debate, you've
had so many commentators,
actually a lot of them real
Trump-hating columnists
and so on, and today, I think yesterday,
Jay Johnson Obama's
Homeland Security Secretary,
all saying some version
of they are effectively open borders,
they are functionally open borders.
You know, critics of Donald
Trump basically saying
this really is the official position now
of the Democratic Party, open borders.
- Well it is, I mean to the point
to where they don't even wanna fund ICE.
They don't even want
to protect the interior
from the open borders that they want.
They are definitely
supportive of open borders,
mainly because, again they need the votes,
but when you have people like AOC
and all of the new Democrats out there
that are pushing these kinds of policies,
it really makes them look even more loony
than they really are,
but they do believe it.
And I mean, and the thing about it is
when you're going into 2020,
I think that the position is very clear,
the voters are gonna have a choice.
You're either gonna vote for America,
or you're gonna vote for a Democrat,
and you can't get any more
clear than that at this point.
- Remember, AOC and the
whole lot of the Democrats
were saying there's no
crisis at the border,
there's no crisis, it's just fiction.
And now they're yelling and screaming
because there isn't enough money
to take care of these people,
well you voted against it, and
you wouldn't support the idea
that they need money at HHS
and Border Patrol
- Oh it's so ridiculous.
- to take care of 'em.
- It's so hypocritical.
Anyway, whatever, there's
more fun to be had
because coming up Joe China is
back doing what he does best,
sticking his foot in his mouth.
We've got the tape and
you're gonna really enjoy it.
That is next.
(upbeat music)
(fast tempo music)
(fast typewriter keystrokes)
- [Narrator] Wildly
adhesive Seasbond seals
give denture wearers 75%
stronger all-day hold.
No reapplying before meals.
Seabond, wildly adhesive.
- [Woman] Dear OxiClean, I live on a farm
with my hard-working
husband, two active kids,
and lots of horses, so I use
OxiClean with odor blasters.
Just one scoop and odor's
gone, thanks OxiClean.
- OxiClean with odor blasters
eliminates tough odors.
- You've got three minutes
to prove how funny you are.
But if you do it, your
life is about to change.
- I get too attached too easily,
I think that's why I can't go to prison.
It's not so much the
showers I'm afraid of,
it's just like what if I fall in love,
you know what I mean?
(laughing)
♪ It's real funny ♪
- Kenan with his run on
SNL, Jeff with standup,
I get to be the voice of the people.
- What happens in Vegas,
stays in Vegas, no it don't.
What happens in Vegas
turned five in February.
- [Man] It's one of the
wildest comedy clubs
I've ever seen.
(audience laughs and cheers)
- [Announcer] Bring the
Funny premieres after AGT.
Check your local listings.
- Let's be honest, you need insurance,
but it's not really
something you wanna buy.
It's not sexy,
- Oh danger.
- or delicious,
(boom)
or fun.
♪ Splashing in the sun ♪
But since you need both
car and home insurance,
why not bundle them with
Esurance and save up to 10%?
Which you can spend on things
you really wanna buy like,
well I don't know what you'd wanna buy,
because I'm just a guy on your TV.
- [Announcer] Esurance,
it's surprisingly painless.
- $120 for the night please.
- $95 for the night please.
- Wait, what?
- If you use Trivago, Trivago
will compare hotel prices
from hundreds of websites worldwide
so you can often find a better
deal for your hotel room.
Maybe you should try Trivago next time.
- [Narrator] Hotel, Trivago.
- When my doctor put me
on a cholesterol-lowering statin drug,
I knew I should take CoQ10
with it, I take Qunol CoQ10.
Why, because Qunol has three times
better absorption than regular CoQ10.
Qunol, the better CoQ10.
- Hi I'm Robert F. Kennedy, Junior.
Recently I was part of a legal
team that won $289 million
for a client who got
non-Hodgkin's lymphoma
from handling Monsanto's
weed killer Roundup.
Most Americans would rather
pull dandelions in their yard
than have their children play in a place
where they're exposed to
a cancer-causing chemical.
But Monsanto decided
not to warn any of us.
If you've been diagnosed
with non-Hodgkin's lymphoma
and you use Roundup
- [Announcer] Call 833-497-8297.
- [Woman] This one is gonna
be a challenge for me.
(dramatic music)
(whooshing)
- [Man] Everything's
moving 100 miles an hour.
- This is your worst nightmare.
(beeping)
(engine revs)
Get out!
Please bring your dish forward.
- [Announcer] Master Chef,
Wednesdays and Thursdays,
or watch anytime on FOX NOW or Hulu.
(upbeat music)
- All right welcome back everyone.
Now Joe Biden, he's done an interview,
always good for a laugh,
we've picked some highlights for you.
Here is the former vice president talking
about world leaders and
how he'd handled them.
- I took on Putin in terms of Iraq,
I mean excuse me in terms of
what was going on in Ukraine.
I've taken on these
leaders around the world.
I'm the guy that's gone in and meant it.
I've taken on all these lead.
- Okay, I'm the guy, he went in there
and took on Putin over
Iraq, whatever it was.
So if you could make out anything
from that sort of rambling incoherence
it was that he stood up to,
but of course he didn't.
They basically did
nothing when Putin walked
into Crimea and Ukraine,
and it's President Trump that
has gotten tough with Russia.
And as for standing up to other countries,
China, I mean my goodness.
Joe Biden when he was vice
president went soft on China,
as we keep telling you,
because the government
put billions of dollars
into his son's businesses.
Anyway, if you thought that
was funny, just watch this.
- Come on man, come on man, come on.
Come here man, come on, come on man.
Hey man, no deal mean.
I'd smack them in the mouth.
- Okay, and then, honestly almost straight
after that he said this.
- I think the American people
want a president who has some dignity.
- Dignity.
(chuckling)
Come on man, I'm gonna
smack you in the mouth.
And he says we need a
president with dignity.
I mean it's just, I don't
know where to start.
- I don't know, I think Uncle
Joe might have taken a nap.
I think he was kinda
sleepy during the debate,
so now he's trying to find his way back.
I mean it was really
interesting when he said
that there wouldn't be
Russia meddling on my watch,
it kinda was your watch guy.
- Right!
- It was funny, you know
I kinda feel sorry for him
at this point, I really do.
(laughing)
He actually bragged about
Obama entrusting him
with the power and authority for Ukraine.
And you've covered extensively
how that went down.
And so I do, I think I just feel sorry
for Uncle Joe at this point.
- The facts are elusive to Joe Biden.
This is what happens when
you're elected in 1972.
He has literally been in that,
in an elected office that long.
I think he is, I think
the Democrats smell blood
in the water, I don't
think he'll be the nominee.
I think they're circling hard,
and I think they just need
to let Joe keep talking
because he's gonna talk
himself right out of it.
There's a reason why he
failed multiple times before
to become the president.
- It's just brilliant.
- There's a reason why
his staffer had to step in
to end the interview
when your staffer
- Is that right?
- has to step in,
- How about during the debate?
- come on.
- How about during the debate
when you say, well I gotta catch an Uber,
or whatever it is that he was saying?
(laughing)
- Oh my time is up.
- It's so bad.
- It's pretty bad.
- You know the thing is it's
just, it makes me laugh,
so President Trump has said,
he doesn't give much away,
but he said, "Actually I'd like
"to face Biden, 'cause he's so terrible."
And a lot oh he's playing
some double game or whatever.
I don't think he is, I
think he really means it
because he's so terrible.
- Yeah, he is, I think it would be great
to see President Trump debate Joe Biden
on stage.
- Oh yes.
People would love.
- We could actually
charge admission for that one incident.
I think it would be quite
a scene for America.
But in all seriousness, Joe
Biden really should reconsider
what he's doing just for his own legacy,
mainly because of all of
the issues that he has.
To Jason's point, he's been
in politics for four decades,
so it's gonna be extremely
hard to constantly
defend his position when every other week
he's gonna have to
apologize for that position,
just because all of
the 30 other contenders
are gonna call him out on it.
- That's right, he should be,
like we were talking
about with Loony Left,
he's just being pushed to
the left the whole time.
Last word, Jason.
- No, Democrats are gonna select somebody,
but the path to get there
is gonna be a hard one.
But if Donald Trump
keeps playing his A game,
he will be reelected I have no doubt.
I think he's stronger politically
today than he's ever been.
- When you see these candidates,
and not just their performance
as with Biden there,
but the policy, in the
end, President Trump won
not just because he was
so strong as a campaigner,
but it was policy, it was the issues
and the arguments he made.
And when you see the
arguments that are coming
from the other side, well.
All right, that's all for tonight.
My thanks to Katrina and
Jason and to you for watching.
You can learn more about
The Next Revolution
by following us @NextRevFNC.
Don't forget to check out the new podcast
at foxnewspodcasts.com with Jason Chaffetz
and his great book "Power
Grab" all written out.
Mark Levin is up next,
see you next Sunday when
The Next Revolution will.