- [Announcer] Everything at
0% interest for 36 months.
So don't wait, hurry in now.
La-Z-Boy Furniture Galleries,
live life comfortably.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] New CBS Sunday,
Brandon Michael Hall
stars in God Friended Me.
- [Carrie Ann] It's
Thursday, February 14th,
Valentine's Day, and The Talk is live.
Empire star, Jussie Smollett,
speaks out for the first time
since his attack last month.
He tells Robin Roberts he's not just angry
at the men who beat him,
he's also outraged at the
skeptics who doubt his story.
Desperate for fame and likes,
a wannabe Instagram
influencer posts herself
throwing a chair off a
building's 45th floor balcony.
Is your sex drive in
sync with your partner's?
One company claims it's
found a way to make sure
you're both in the mood
with no risk of rejection.
Justin Bieber is reportedly being treated
for deep depression issues.
Find out how his wife,
Hailey, is helping him
and what they are putting on hold.
Then our neighborhood is about
to get a whole lot funnier
thanks to the stars of the hit
CBS show "The Neighborhood".
Cedric The Entertainer and
Tichina Arnold are here.
So let's start talking.
♪ We can talk it, we can talk it out ♪
♪ So what you got what you got ♪
♪ What you got now ♪
♪ We got now ♪
♪ So let's talk it out ♪
- Hello and welcome to The Talk.
Happy Valentine's Day, everybody.
(cheering)
Let's get started with Empire.
- [Audience Member] Happy Valentine's Day!
- Happy Valentine's Day.
- All right, let's get
started with Empire star
Jussie Smollett, speaking
out for the first time
after his attack.
It's been two and a
half weeks since Jussie
said he was attacked in Chicago by two men
who yelled racial and homophobic slurs,
punched him, wrapped a
rope around his neck,
and then doused him with bleach.
Because police said
Jussie initially refused
to turn over his phone records
and that the ones he
did eventually give them
were heavily edited and redacted,
some people have accused
the Empire star of lying.
Today Jussie sat down
with GMA's Robin Roberts
to set the record straight.
- I'm pissed off.
- What is it that has you so angry?
Is it the attackers?
- It's the attackers, but
it's also the attacks.
Wanting me to give my phone to the tech
for three to four hours.
I'm sorry but
I'm not going to do that.
- Why?
- Because I have private
pictures and videos and numbers.
My partner's number, my family's number,
my castmates' number, my friends' numbers,
my private emails, my private
songs, my private voice memos.
I don't know what that's gonna
be to hand over my phone.
(clapping)
- While Chicago Police have
screened lots of footage
from neighborhood security cameras,
they still have not found
video of the actual attack.
Jussie shared his frustration.
- I want that video found so badly
because for probably four reasons.
Number one, I want them to
find the people that did it.
Number two, I want them to stop
being able to say alleged attack.
Number three, I want them
to see that I fought back,
and I want a little gay
boy who might watch this
to see that I fought the (beeping) back.
It does not take anything away from people
that are not able to do
that, but I fought back.
They ran off, I didn't.
(audience applauds)
- And we have this new
update from Chicago Police
who announced they are questioning
two persons of interest in
connection with Jussie's attack.
Police stress neither person
has been charged with a crime,
and as of now, there is no
evidence they were involved.
So do you think speaking
out is the best way
to shut down skeptics?
- [Audience] Yes!
- Oh absolutely, and I've
got to side with Jussie
on the thing that I don't
want my phone to be looked at.
All my nude shots and things.
(audience laughs)
- More specific--
- Yes!
(cheering)
Hours and hours.
Hours and hours of
sexual footage of myself.
I wouldn't want my phone to
be taken away and analyzed.
I just wouldn't want it.
Not for anything other than
it's my personal life on there,
and I just wouldn't want it,
so I totally get that with him.
And I totally get that he
might have deleted some things.
It's hard, he's been
through a really tough time.
- Yeah, and the media has
really cast so much doubt
on his story, which I find
so personally offensive.
That a gay black man is targeted,
and then suddenly he becomes the victim
of people's disbelief.
(audience applauds)
It's so outrageous to me.
There have been things like well
why would he be getting a
Subway sandwich at two a.m.
He said himself, well
they're open at that time
because people go; otherwise,
they wouldn't be open.
- We go.
- I go.
- Or people say in that neighborhood
you couldn't get a taxi.
Says who?
It's just like these
sort of ridiculous things
where I feel like why don't
we believe this person, why?
- It really is sad, and with
all that he has been through,
the fact that he has to come out.
But at the same time,
because of social media,
there are so many opinions,
it's better to hear it
from his own mouth and hear it from him
and feel his energy, and I'm glad
with everything that has happened,
I am happy that he's
being brave enough to sit
with Robin Roberts and share his story.
- And if the naysayers know so much
about what they think happened,
why you don't know who did it?
- Exactly.
Since you know so much,
since you know so much,
just tell us what you know.
I hate the fact that we
are in a social media.
Even the common person.
Usually it's the celebrity and their fans
and their followers.
Now it's even the common
person who may have something
happen to them that they're
going to their supporters
or whatever for acknowledgement.
That's why people don't want to talk.
That's why people don't
want to come forward.
Because they're gonna be judged.
And that doesn't help the situation.
- Well what I hope that the
police are on to something
with these two persons of interest.
I hope they get them, and
that people have to look at
how as a media and as
culture we twist things
and cast doubt on things that
we should not cast doubt on.
(audience applauds)
- And hear them apologize,
will people apologize.
When the truth come
out, will you apologize?
As hard as you judged
him, will you apologize?
(audience applauds)
- Hope so, but I doubt it.
- In other news, a 19-year-old
wannabe Instagram influencer
with less than 4,000 followers
threw two chairs off a 45th-story balcony
in Toronto over the weekend,
presumably to get more likes.
Now she's been arrested.
The CBC has details.
(audience applauds)
- [News Anchor] The
video of a woman tossing
a patio chair off the balcony
of a Toronto high rise
takes your breath away.
(woman gasps)
People are stunned as they
see it for the first time.
- It's ridiculous, why risk peoples' lives
for a moment of just
Internet fame essentially?
- [News Anchor] Below that balcony,
the Gardiner Expressway
and lots of foot traffic.
Police think it was two chairs,
found crumpled in a heap
at the base of the building.
- She has been charged
with endangering life
and has now been released on $1,500 bail
and ordered to live with her mother.
So do you think all social media platforms
should ban her for life?
- [Audience] Yes!
- Oh yeah, I mean here
is a perfect example
of a young person who wants instant fame,
the recognition, everything
that comes with it,
for nothing except being
stupid, ignorant, no talent.
Why would you, 45, I can't even believe
that the window opened on the 45th floor,
but, however, it did, and her chucking.
Can you imagine if that had hit a car
and that car would have
crashed into another car
and another and another?
I mean, the thought of
it just makes you shiver.
It's just ridiculous that
these wannabe kids out there
think overnight they're
going to get fame and fortune
for being pathetic.
You are a pathetic young girl.
(audience applauds)
She wants to be an influencer.
Well why don't you work on your writing.
You want to influence
people, work on something.
You don't get something
worth having overnight
by being ridiculously ignorant as you are.
- It's sad.
- Yeah, and it's over likes.
That's not even a real thing, people.
(audience applauds)
Priyanka Chopra Jonas
costars in the new rom-com,
"Isn't It Romantic".
She tells Extra that her
new husband, Nick Jonas,
is super romantic, take a look.
- You haven't been married for too long,
but what is the most romantic thing
in the theme of "Isn't It Romantic"
that he's done for you?
- Oh my god, the night before
we were getting married,
I was doing a bridesmaid's
hangout in my room.
When we opened my room to come in,
there was a lane of flowers all the way
with about 18 or 19 gifts
with little notes on each one,
like I will protect you, I
will always keep you safe.
It was just like, everyone was crying.
- He wins, that's amazing.
- He does.
He wins life.
(cheering)
- What's the most romantic thing anyone's
ever done for you?
- For me, my husband is the
king at romantic gestures.
He's on his way to come see me right now.
This morning I woke up, and he posted this
before his flight.
And I'm like it just melts my heart
because honestly he's amazing.
He is just great.
(audience applauds)
- Aw, romance.
I like romance.
- Audience, tell me, how can
I get this kind of romance?
I wanna ask the audience,
what do you think guys?
How am I going to get that
kind of romance in my life?
Anyone, nobody has any suggestions?
Any suggestions?
- You're out of luck.
- Any advice please?
Yes, yes, yes, ma'am?
- I'm so nervous, I'm so excited.
- Come on down.
- So excited.
- My name is Vanessa, and
I wanted to sing a song
to my fiance.
(cheering)
Oh my god, I'm so scared.
- I don't know who that is.
♪ Hi Dolly, I love you ♪
♪ I'm making bad right now ♪
(audience applauds)
- You look gorgeous.
- So surprised.
(cheering)
- When we walked out, I was
like looking at the ceiling,
what's going to drop, which
person is she gonna to be.
- Look what I did.
- Oh my god.
- Look what I did for
her, I covered my tattoos.
(audience applauds)
I tried to get rid of my gap for her.
- Before we came out, again,
I looked at the schedule
like no, she's got a
meeting from 10:30 to 12,
she can't torture me on the air.
- Happy Valentine's Day.
(audience applauds)
- [Announcer] Great
guests, big give-aways.
Go to TheTalk.com for tickets.
[Male] If you are 65 or older,
even if you're healthy you
may be at increased risk
for pneumococcal pneumonia,
a potentially serious
bacterial lung disease that can
disrupt your life for weeks.
In severe cases, pneumococcal pneumonia
can put you in the hospital.
It may take weeks to
recover, making you miss out
on the things you enjoy most.
Just one dose of the Prevnar 13 vaccine
can help protect you from
pneumococcal pneumonia.
It's not a yearly shot.
Prevnar 13 is approved for
adults to help prevent infections
from 13 strains of the bacteria
that cause pneumococcal pneumonia.
Don't get Prevnar 13 if you have had
a severe allergic reaction
to the vaccine or its ingredients.
Adults with weakened immune systems
may have a lower response to the vaccine.
The most common side effects were pain,
redness and swelling
at the injection site,
limited arm movement, fatigue,
headache, muscle pain,
joint pain, less appetite, vomiting,
fever, chills, and rash.
Prevention begins with Prevnar 13.
Ask your doctor or
pharmacist about Prevnar 13.
- [Male Narrator] When
cravings hit, hit back.
Choose Glucerna, with slow-release carbs
to help manage blood sugar,
and start making every day progress.
Glucerna.
- [Announcer] Unwanted odors lingering
too long in your car?
Try Febreze Car vent clips.
Just snap the clip and insert in the vent
to eliminate lingering
odors for up to 30 days.
Try Febreze car vent clips.
Available in a range of
light to bold scents.
- [Announcer] Brushing only
reaches 25% of your mouth.
Listerine cleans virtually 100%,
helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%, always go for 100.
Bring out the bold.
- [Announcer] Macy's Presidents'
Day Sale starts tomorrow.
Take an extra 20% off with
your Macy's card or pass.
Save 20 to 60% on
furniture and mattresses.
And Levis for all just $17.99 to $49.99.
Plus Macy's Star Rewards members
can earn toward Star money.
- [Announcer] Our grandparents
checked their Smartphones
zero times a day.
Times change, eyes haven't.
That's why there's Ocuvite.
Screen light, sun light, longer hours.
Eyes today are stressed.
But Ocuvite has vital
nutrients to help protect them.
Ocuvite, eye nutrition for today.
- [Announcer] This is Ragu Simply.
Simply made with 100% olive oil.
Simply no sugar added.
Simply dinner.
Simply delicious.
Ragu Simply.
- [Announcer] Tonight.
- Stronger together.
He stole Hillary
Clinton's campaign slogan.
It's only a matter of time
before he steals her look.
- Colbert's all new with Bradley Cooper.
- [Announcer] Melissa
McCarthy and the secret life
of George Washington, this Sunday morning.
(audience applauds)
- Are you ever in the mood but
aren't sure your partner is?
An Ohio couple has come
up with a unique solution.
They call it LoveSync.
And they're raising money
for it on Kick Starter.
Take a look.
Love Sync is a device that lets you know
when both of you are in the
mood for some hippity-dippity.
- It's super simple.
All you have to do is place a button
at each of your bedsides.
And when you're feeling a little randy,
you just anonymously push the button.
There is no risk of rejection.
If only one of you pushes
the button, nothing happens,
and your partner is none the wiser.
But, if your partner's also
ready for a pants off dance off,
they'll press their button.
The Love Sync technology
combines these anonymous inputs
and recognizes that there is consensus.
It lets you both know by
emitting a swirling glow
from the buttons.
(audience laughs)
- Serious question, do you
feel like you and your mate's
sex drives are in sync?
- Well first, the button is unnecessary.
Why don't you just poke me in the back
or tap me on the shoulder
like most people do?
(audience applauds)
I got enough gadgets in my nightstand.
I don't need this button.
- I was just saying to the girls,
I think it's gonna be like
a joke gift to give out
for birthday gifts or when
someone's getting married.
A silly little novelty gift.
I think it's gonna be like the pet rock.
Useless, but everybody got one.
(audience laughs)
- I think it's kind of
cute for some reason.
I think it's kind of
cute, but I can also see
a fight between people like
I pushed my button!
(audience laughs)
- There is no way for rejection,
but there is rejection.
- There is rejection.
- If the person doesn't
push the button back,
you feel some type of way, it's weird.
- Since Linda was just out here,
are you and Linda's sex drives in sync?
Would you tap your
buttons at the same time?
- I'm not going to answer
those kinds of questions.
- Here's the bigger story part.
So what if you're pressing the button,
but I'm asleep and I don't
see you pressing the button?
Or what if the button gets jammed?
(laughing)
- Well, they're not that far away
that they can't unjam at you.
- I'd rather use my batteries
for other things child.
(audience applauds)
- There are people who are
more forthcoming than I am.
Have you guys ever had relationships
where you're in sync
or not in sync?
- I've had both, I've had both.
Me and Max are pretty good.
- These are things on
your mind for later today.
The one that got away that I think about
that was like my first
love when I was about 23,
our sex drives were absolutely in sync.
And I had a really good
girlfriend in Hawaii
once tell me, and her
relationship has been going on,
I put all my energy towards my career,
but her, she's put all her
energy towards her like marriage
and her love life, and she
says that the sex drive
is the most important thing
because it's how you sort of
keep coming back together,
that divine attraction
on all levels, right?
- I had a guy who was so out
of sync that I would stay up
all night just so I
didn't have to do nothing.
And then I would sleep all day.
I'd drink coffee.
- How long was this relationship?
- Every time this guy calls me,
and he normally calls
around Valentine's Day,
you know I'm busy I can't.
I never thought I would be
out of sync with this guy.
- He's going to take his button
and just hit you over the head with it.
- We'll be right back.
(audience applauds)
- [Announcer] You know that look,
that life of the party look?
Walk it off look.
One more mile look.
Reply all look.
Own your look with fewer lines.
There's only one Botox Cosmetic.
It's the only one FDA
approved to temporarily make
frown lines, crows feet, and
forehead lines look better.
The effects of Botox
Cosmetic may spread hours
to weeks after injection,
causing serious symptoms.
Alert your doctor right away,
as difficulty swallowing,
speaking, breathing, eye
problems, or muscle weakness
may be a sign of a
life-threatening condition.
Do not receive Botox Cosmetic
if you have a skin infection.
Side effects may include
allergic reactions,
injection site pain, headache,
eyebrow eyelid drooping,
and eyelid swelling.
Tell your doctor about
your medical history,
muscle or nerve conditions,
and medications,
including botulinum toxins,
as these may increase the
risk of serious side effects.
So give that just saw a puppy look
and whatever that look is.
Look like you with fewer lines.
Own your look with the one
and only Botox Cosmetic.
- [Announcer] Those arms,
they'll be jelly tomorrow.
It'll hurt to sit and laugh
because that workout is working.
Feed it with Special K.
With iron, protein, and B vitamins.
Feed your progress, feed
your power, feed your change.
- [Announcer] I was thrilled to be able
to go with my friends to
our annual get-together,
especially after being diagnosed
last year with advanced
non-small cell lung cancer.
- [Announcer] Another
true story with Keytruda.
- I started Katie on
Keytruda and chemotherapy,
and she's getting results we
rarely saw five years ago.
- [Announcer] In a clinical trial,
significantly more patients
lived longer and saw their tumors shrink
than on chemotherapy alone.
- It has changed my approach
to treating patients.
- [Announcer] Keytruda may be used
with certain chemotherapies
as your first treatment
if you have advanced non squamous
non-small cell lung cancer
and you do not have an
abnormal EGFR or ALK gene.
Keytruda helps your
immune system fight cancer
but can also cause your immune system
to attack healthy parts of your body.
This can happen during or after treatment
and may be severe and lead to death.
See your doctor right away if
you have new or worse cough,
chest pain, shortness of breath, diarrhea,
severe stomach pain or
tenderness, nausea or vomiting,
rapid heartbeat, increased
hunger or thirst,
constipation, dizziness or fainting,
changes in urine or eyesight,
muscle pain or weakness, joint pain,
confusion or memory problems,
fever, rash, itching, or flushing.
These are not all the
possible side effects.
Tell your doctor about all
your medical conditions,
including immune system problems,
if you've had an organ transplant,
had or plan to have a
stem cell transplant,
or have lung, breathing,
or liver problems.
- Where I am now, compared to a year ago,
it's a story worth sharing.
- [Announcer] Living longer is possible.
It's true, Keytruda from Merck,
with more FDA-approved uses
for advanced lung cancer
than any other immunotherapy.
(audience applauds)
- Justin Bieber is reportedly
putting his wedding plans
on hold because of his mental health.
Justin and his wife Hailey were married
in a secret civil ceremony last year
and had planned to say "I Do"
again in a religious service,
but those plans were delayed while Justin
seeks counseling for his depression.
A source tells People
Magazine that the 24-year-old
has felt overwhelmed by fame.
The source says "being
followed, having his every move
stalked by fans, cameras in
his face, it all sets him off,
and he often feels like
everyone is out to get him."
Have you ever had to put something on hold
to focus on your mental health?
- [All] Yeah.
- I think that most of us have.
When life becomes, you lose
control of what's going on,
and you just think I can't do it, I can't.
I need to take a breath.
I feel badly for him because
I know that a lot of people
are probably saying, well
what's he depressed about?
He's got everything, he's got
this, that, and the other,
and it just doesn't work that
way with severe depression,
it really doesn't, and I feel
really bad for him right now.
I am happy that he's
getting himself together,
his head together, his
priorities, he's got right.
And I'm glad he's taking
a break for himself.
(audience applauds)
- There was a time once when I felt like,
my father died right before a season
of Dancing with the Stars,
like four days before.
As much as I felt myself
going into depression,
but I had to put it off.
Have you ever done this as well?
Where there's like a
time where I had to put
like a steel wall between
me and my emotions
so I could get through the season
of Dancing with the Stars
and everything that was coming.
I had just broken up with
my fiance, my dad died,
I moved, I was diagnosed
with chronic illness.
It was one of those times that
I knew I didn't have time.
What was important is you
shouldn't push off your emotions
unless you know you can
have a time to deal with it.
That's the part that was key.
I knew after the season was over,
I could spend like three months
just sort of taking care of myself,
and I was very fortunate to have that.
I've had it almost the opposite.
- Did you feel during that
time that you were acting out
at all or having weird
emotions kind of sneak out?
- Yeah, they do sneak out,
because emotions are emotions.
They have their own template,
their own desires that come out,
and they will find a way out.
You can put them off for like.
Dancing with the Stars is
like 10 weeks out of the year.
So for 10 weeks I could
kind of put them on hold,
but they would sneak out.
I would watch Dance.
Andy Dick was on our show that year.
He danced something, I like lost it.
It was really simple,
it was my own emotions
with my own life coming up.
- But then what did you
do once you had that time?
- I actually sought counseling.
I love to read.
There are so many great
books that you can read.
I bought every book I could
possibly find on depression.
I just went and sought my friends,
my support system, I was very lucky.
We'll be right back.
(audience applauds)
- Heavenly hand cream.
- Heavenly hand cream?
My hands get so dry and
cracked, I need serious relief.
That's why I use O'Keefe's Working Hands.
It's America's number
one selling hand cream.
For guaranteed relief of
dry and cracked hands.
Thanks to O'Keefe's, I got my hands back.
- Millions of people across
the country are losing weight
and improving their health.
What do we all have in common?
Nutrisystem.
- [Announcer] Introducing new
FrehStart from Nutrisystem.
Jumpstart your weight loss
and your healthy lifestyle.
Our chefs create your
favorite foods made healthier.
Perfectly balanced to put
your body in fat burning mode.
Lose weight naturally.
I lost 50 pounds with Nutrisystem.
- [Announcer] Lose up to 13
pounds and 7 inches overall
in your first month.
- I can even eat out
with family and friends.
- [Announcer] Call or go
online right now and save 40%.
- I'm doing things now that
I never thought I could.
- [Announcer] Order
today and we'll rush you
Nutrisystem FreshStart plus a week
of all-new FreshStart shakes free.
High protein designed to burn fat,
with probiotics to shrink your belly.
Plus FedEx shipping free.
Try us, money back guarantee.
- Join the millions who have lost weight
and improved their health.
Call or go online right now.
- [Announcer] Go online or
call 866-990-Fit7 right now
and save 40%, plus get
probiotic shakes free.
- [Announcer] It's Macy's
Presidents' Day Sale,
with specials Friday through Monday.
Like 40% off shoes and boots for her,
coats 49.99 to 89.99,
and designer pillows or towels only 5.99.
Tomorrow at Macy's.
- [Announcer] So, there you
are with your depression.
And your dirty laundry
that you just don't want to deal with.
Because depression is multiple symptoms.
Yeah, time for a change.
And your doctor tells
you about Trintellix.
A prescription medicine for depression.
So you're feeling this overall relief
and Trintellix had no significant impact
on weight in clinical trials.
You got this.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have worsening depression,
unusual changes in mood, behavior,
or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants can
increase these in children,
teens, and young adults.
Do not take with MAOIs.
Tell your doctor about your medications,
including migraine, psychiatric,
and depression medications
to avoid a potentially
life-threatening condition.
Increased risk of bleeding
and bruising may occur,
especially if taken with
NSAID pain relievers,
aspirin, or blood thinners.
Manic episodes or vision problems
may occur in some people.
May cause low sodium levels.
Common side effects include
nausea, constipation, and vomiting.
- [Announcer] Not living in sweat pants.
- [Announcer] Ask your doctor
about changing to Trintellix.
- Drop it right now.
- You took my son's life.
- Sorry boss, we got a problem.
- [Announcer] Don't
miss "The Neighborhood".
New CBS Monday, eight, seven central.
- They say...
- They say.
- They say in D.C.
- We just can't get things done.
- We say.
- This is where idealists come together.
- And history inspires us to greatness.
- So what matters.
- What they say
- Or what's real?
- [Announcer] Have you been
hurt in a car accident?
- Motorcycle accident?
- Or a big truck accident?
- When you are hurt in
any kind of accident
you have a lawyer.
- That's right, when you need
a lawyer, you have a lawyer.
No matter what kind of
accident you've been in,
call us at Saiontz and Kirk
or go to YouHaveALawyer.com.
- Any time, anywhere, 24/7,
days, nights, or weekends.
When you've been hurt,
and you need a lawyer.
- You have a lawyer.
- 1-800-Lawyers or YouHaveALawyer.com.
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-Lawyers
or visit YouHaveALawyer.com.
If you have a phone, you have a lawyer.
- Is your house less than perfect?
I am Dan from MarketPro Home Buyers,
and we want to buy your home.
Don't make repairs, don't pay commissions,
and don't wait another day.
We'll get you the cash you need.
No agent fees, no closing costs.
We'll even help you
pack and move for free.
For a no-obligation
offer, call 301-799-SELL.
That's 301-799-7355, or visit
MarketProHomeBuyers.com.
We buy houses as is, on
your schedule, call today.
- I'm Darren Haynes,
catch my take on sports
right here, on WSA9.
(audience applauds)
- With harsh winter storms
affecting nearly every part
of the country this week,
snowball fights are a common occurrence,
but one Seattle woman got arrested
after she nearly ran
over a group of people
who allegedly threw snowballs at her car.
The local CBS station has details.
(yelling)
- [News Anchor] Joey Wiser
shot this cellphone video
that's now gone viral.
(woman yelling)
- He told me he couldn't believe
the woman behind the wheel
of this blue Jeep would swerve past him
before running straight
into a group of people
across the street, narrowly missing them.
- It seems like her intention
was to run them over.
- It was a neighborhood
snowball fight that went wrong.
- [News Anchor] Rocky Moran was
the person seen in the video
trying to hold the woman down.
He said that she got upset because her car
was hit by one of the snowballs.
The woman's car ended up
getting stuck in the snow.
Neighbors called police, and her arrest
was also caught on camera.
Authorities said the woman now
identified is facing charges
of DUI and reckless driving.
- Oh my gosh, what is wrong with people?
What is wrong with her?
People need to calm down.
You don't go after somebody with your car,
a vehicle that could kill people,
when you were hit by a
snowball, it's just ridiculous.
- And the thing is, she could
have lost control of that car,
in the snow, so it's so ridiculous.
- I'm glad nobody got
hurt, but I'm also glad
that she was caught because
she was drinking and driving.
So at least she got arrested.
So I'm glad she did do what she did.
- It's a good reminder about
these kind of videos everywhere, right?
Even if you're not drunk.
When I was at the Grammys the other day
I was trying to see Linda
perform her section with Dolly,
and I was backstage with her,
and then I went to go
get seated during it.
And they kept saying,
oh it's a commercial,
you can't go in, okay now
you can't sit in your seat,
and I was like, you know those moments
where you're like, I have to.
I was like cool it Sara,
because there's videos everywhere.
It's like you learn.
Not that I would anyway, but
you just can't take your life
out on other people, which
is what I always think
these things are.
Something else is bothering this person.
(audience applauds)
- It's a little
neighborhood snowball fight.
Why didn't you get involved in the fight?
She could have jumped out the car,
balled a snowball up, and said I got you
and then hit them.
Then it would have been
fun in the neighborhood.
We're just not neighbors anymore.
- Maybe it would have sobered her up too.
- To be out in the cold in that snow.
- We think of everything.
- Sober up and don't run people over.
We'll be right back.
(audience applauds)
- [Announcer] Coming up next,
from "The Neighborhood" to our table,
Cedric The Entertainer and Tichina Arnold.
(audience applauds)
- Are you ready for this?
- She doesn't like it.
You gotta get in there.
Be careful not to get it in her eyes.
(baby crying)
- I know what a bath is.
- Smile honey.
- First kid.
- Here we go.
- Second kid.
- Coming in, Mommy?
- Not a chance.
- By their second kid,
every parent is an expert
and more likely to choose
Luvs than first-time parents.
Luvs with Night Luv Plus
absorbs wetness faster
than Huggies Snug and Dry.
For outstanding overnight protection
at a fraction of the cost.
Live, learn, and get Luvs.
- On tour, every second counts.
I need great, without the weight.
- [Announcer] New Elvive Rapid
Reviver Deep Conditioners.
L'Oreal's patented conditioners work fast,
with no leave-in time.
Enriched with damage-repairing serum.
Two times easier detangling.
Two times less breakage than
with the leading conditioner.
Works deep, repaires damage fast.
Hair is transformed instantly.
New Rapid Reviver Deep Conditioners.
Elvive revives damaged hair.
We're worth it.
- Wow, I'm in really great shape.
My PT says I'm in the top
5% fittest in the state.
Fun fact, I have a huge office.
- [Announcer] Make this
Valentine's sweeter than ever.
New special event download now.
- Metastatic breast cancer is relentless,
but I'm relentless too.
- MBC doesn't take a day
off, and neither will I.
- I treat my MBC with every-day Verzenio,
the only one of its kind
that can be taken every day.
Verzenio is the only CDK
four and six inhibitor,
approved with hormonal therapy
that can be taken every day
for postmenopausal women with
HR-positive HER2-negative MBC.
Verzenio plus an AI helped women
have significantly more time
without disease progression,
and more than half of women
saw their tumors shrink
versus an AI.
Diarrhea is common, may be severe,
or cause dehydration or infection.
Before taking Verzenio, tell your doctor
if you have fever, chills,
or other signs of infection.
Verzenio may cause low
white blood cell counts,
which may cause serious
infection that can lead to death.
Serious liver problems can occur.
Symptoms include tiredness,
appetite loss, stomach pain,
and bleeding or bruising.
Blood clots that can lead
to death have occurred.
Tell your doctor if you
have pain or swelling
in your arms or legs, shortness
of breath, chest pain,
rapid breathing or heart
rate, or if you are pregnant,
nursing, or plan to be pregnant.
Common side effects
include nausea, infections,
low blood cells and
platelets, decreased appetite,
headache, abdominal pain, tiredness,
vomiting, and hair thinning or loss.
- I am relentless, and my
doctor and I choose to treat
my metastatic breast cancer with Verzenio.
- [Announcer] Ask your doctor
about every-day Verzenio.
- [Announcer] Yeah, getting
your 10 grams of Silk protein.
- Yeah.
- Feels good.
- [Announcer] You're doing it,
you're going to slay today.
- Yeah.
- [Announcer] You're spilling.
- [Announcer] It's
okay, it's all progress.
Silk.
- [Female Announcer] Nivea
essentially enriched body lotion
with two times the almond oil.
It deeply nourishes skin for 48 hours.
♪ One two three woo ♪
- Niva essentially enriched.
Deeply nourishes for 48 hours.
- Officer shot.
- [Announcer] Tensions in L.A.
- L.A.P.D., get down!
- [Announcer] Reach a boiling point.
- We can't hold them, there's too many.
- Fall back.
- New S.W.A.T., CBS tonight.
- [Male Announcer] Malcolm's new job.
- That's my boy right there.
- [Male Announcer] brings
pride to "The Neighborhood".
- These are your dad's.
- Yep, they sure are.
- [Male Announcer] New
episode, CBS Monday.
An extreme twist will push
the castaways to their limits.
- [Male Player] This game
will take everything from you.
- A new Survivor premieres CBS Wednesday.
- Our next guests crack
us up every Monday night
as happily and hilariously married couple
Tina and Calvin Butler
on the hit CBS comedy, "The Neighborhood".
(audience applauds)
In next week's episode,
they team up to give
their adult son a pep talk
about his new job, take a look.
- I don't know Pop.
I ain't never worked in sales before.
- Well you're in luck.
I mean I've had my auto shop for 30 years.
I can teach you all
about the ABCs of sales.
Always be Calvin.
(audience laughs)
- You mean be grouchy and always forget
to put the toilet seat down?
- No babe.
Be confident, be charming,
and always make it
about the customer's needs.
- This customer really needs
you to put the toilet seat down.
- Please welcome our good friends,
Tichina Arnold and Cedric The Entertainer.
(audience applauds)
- Congratulations are in
order because, Cedric,
you were just nominated
for a NAACP Image Award.
- Yes he was!
(audience cheers)
And congratulations to both of you
because "The Neighborhood"
has already been renewed
for its second season
(audience applauds)
and we have the moment that it happened.
We have the moment that
you guys found out.
So Tichina, what was
going through your mind?
- My daughter's tuition.
We're regular people,
we're just working actors.
We're blessed to be working.
Beth loves twerking, she
twerks at every possibility.
- On the show itself, Max
Greenfield and Beth Behrs
play your white neighbors,
the only white couple
in "The Neighborhood", but Cedric,
I heard when you moved
to L.A., you sort of had
a similar fish-out-of-water experience.
- Yeah, I moved into an
all-Latino neighborhood
when I first moved to L.A.,
so I had to learn there's a
lot of food going come over.
It's a lot of cooking going on.
Corn with sauce and
mayonnaise and all that.
I didn't know what was going on.
But it was cool though.
- Then you actually, your Walk of Fame.
- My star on the Walk of Fame.
- Yes.
- I used to walk around there of course
and see all these stars.
You just come to Hollywood from St. Louis.
And so now, when I got my star,
I was literally a block over from where
I first moved to L.A.
That was just kind of like so cool.
(audience applauds)
- Hi Sharon.
- Hi Tichina.
You and Cedric have been
playing husband and wife
for a year now.
- Yes.
Does any of that like go on
off when you're not working?
Do you take care of him?
- Oh most definitely, I
don't play with his wife.
Lorna does not play,
and I fill her shoes
as best as I can when he's on that set.
So I make sure that he rests.
You know he takes moments.
I didn't tell you
I took a video of you
snoring the other day.
People don't realize this
man runs a whole show
but he's also on the road.
So he's doing comedy on weekends.
I gotta take care of my Boo, my Set Boo,
I make sure he's all right.
Cedric is just such an
amazing human being.
Like literally this man I've
known for 20-something years.
This is the first time he
and I have worked together.
I have seen this man treat
everybody with respect.
From the person that moves the cables.
To the first person there
in the morning on our set.
He treats everybody the same.
So I'm happy to have him as my friend.
(audience applauds)
- The great Marla Gibbs,
who we all know from 227,
was guest on the show this week.
So Cedric, what was it
like working with her?
- I mean, of course,
Marla Gibbs, is an icon.
I was always a fan of 227,
but when she was on The Jeffersons.
I wanted to get into a
little riff with her.
She was funny though.
She is so great, so gracious.
It was just awesome to
have her on the set.
This iconic personality.
She loved it, she loved being at work.
And to have been doing it for so long
that it was just really awesome for us
to be able to provide that opportunity.
She had a great time.
- And she was off book.
Marla has done a lot
for the black community.
She has done amazing work
- Pretty incredible, but
last week on the episode,
there featured a girls' trip
to a Magic Mike show in Las Vegas.
Did you crash the party a little there?
(crosstalk drowns out conversation)
- Saying hello to the gentlemen.
- Look at Ced, look at Ced.
- And then I pulled a hamstring.
(audience applauds)
- I got a little bit...
The guys were a little nervous
about taking their shirts off,
and so I said guys let
me show you how its done.
- You dance, you sing, you
dance, you do all that.
(audience applauds excitedly)
- To get through college,
I was known as Cupcakes.
- Ceddy, I got to see you just recently.
You were hosting the "Motown 60",
a Grammy celebration,
which was incredible.
It airs on April 21st, and you co-hosted
with Mr. Smokey Robinson
and so many other incredible performers.
Did you get to hang out with anybody
or see anybody that you never met before?
- The only person I really
was stalking was Diana Ross,
and I guess it got pretty
obvious that I was stalking her
'cause her security wouldn't let me get
close enough, you know.
But I did the whole,
went to Berry Gordy first and then,
"Hey Diana, how you doing?"
Tried it but they wouldn't
let me get close to her.
- But why?
- I don't know.
- I would have called Tracy,
we should have called Tracy.
Tell your Mama we looking for her!
- Tichina let me ask you something
that everybody's been looking for
is the Martin reboot.
(audience applauds)
- Everybody's waiting for that
What can you tell us, what can you share?
- I will share that Martin
called me about a month ago,
and he got some good
news about a huge network
wanting to take it on, so
we'll see, fingers crossed.
But it will never be
the same without Tommy.
Martin's show will never
be the same without Tommy,
so it's not a reboot, I call it a rebirth.
- When we come back we have
a Valentine's Day challenge that will test
the foundation of Cedric
and Tichina's TV marriage.
Get ready to play Husband and
Wife but not in Real Life.
(audience applauds)
- [Male Announcer] When
you eat a bowl of oatmeal,
you're getting Beta Glucan.
That's a soluble fiber that slows
the breakdown of carbohydrates,
and that provides energy that lasts.
- Only one OTC topical
pain reliever's label
claims we're FDA approved, just
like prescription medicines.
New Salonpas Patch large.
Uniquely labeled to treat
mild to tough or moderate pain
for up to 12 hours.
Salonpas, power without a prescription.
- [Female Announcer] It's
Macy's Valentine's Day Sale.
Give the wonder of love
and save on watches,
fine jewelry, and more.
Plus get an extra 20% off
with your Macy's card or savings pass.
Now at Macy's.
- My mom washes the dishes
before she puts them
in the dishwasher, so what
does the dishwasher do?
- Cascade Platinum does the work for you,
pre-washing and removing
stuck-on foods the first time.
- Wow, that's clean.
- Cascade Platinum.
- [Announcer] The day
after chemo shouldn't mean
going back to the doctor just for a shot.
With Neulasta Onpro,
patients get their day back.
To be with family or just to sleep in.
Strong chemo can put you at
risk of serious infection.
In a key study, Neulasta reduced the risk
of infection for 17%
to 1%, a 94% decrease.
Neulasta Onpro is designed
to deliver Neulasta
the day after chemo and is
used by most patients today.
- [Announcer] Neulasta is
for certain cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta if
you are allergic to it
or Neupogen, filgrastim.
An incomplete dose could
increase infection risk.
Ruptured spleen, sometimes fatal
as well as serious lung problems,
allergic reactions, kidney injury,
and capillary leak syndrome have occurred.
Report abdominal or shoulder tip pain,
trouble breathing or allergic reactions
to your doctor right away.
In patients with Sickle Cell Disorder,
serious, sometimes
fatal, crises can occur.
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
- [Announcer] Ask your
doctor about Neulasta Onpro.
Pay no more than $5 per
dose with copay card.
- 90% of women have a skin care routine,
but what about a lip care routine?
Pay your lips some attention.
The Chapstick total hydration collection.
Exfoliate, nourish,
naturally enhance your lips.
Chapstick, put your lips first.
♪ When you have nausea,
heartburn, indigestion ♪
♪ Upset stomach, diarrhea ♪
- [Announcer] Girl, Pepto Ultra Coating
will treat your stomach right.
♪ Nausea, heartburn, indigestion ♪
♪ Upset stomach, diarrhea ♪
- Try Pepto with Ultra Coating
- [Announcer] In an era of online retail
where everything is
just a few clicks away,
buying a car should be no different.
That's why at Carvana you
can buy a car 100% online.
We made it easy to browse, view, and buy
from over 10,000 cars.
You can even trade in your old car,
all while binge watching
your favorite TV show.
Afterwards, we'll deliver your car to you,
or you can pick it up from one
of our car vending machines.
Either way, your car comes
with a seven-day return policy.
So grab a seat, relax in your comfy pants,
and enjoy the new way to
buy a car, at Carvana.
- [Announcer] Had enough
of comedy that's quiet,
ironic, and understated?
(screaming)
- Or do you just want funny?
- You know that chicken isn't meat.
- Are you sure?
It's small and skinny and a little bitter.
- Comedy that makes you laugh.
- Jokey, joke, joke, ha, he, ho, ooh.
- What a concept.
(screaming)
- A new Fam after a new Mom, CBS tonight.
(audience applauds)
- [Announcer] Additional
sponsorship provided by.
(squirting)
- Guess I'll bring a can
of this stuff everywhere.
- [Female Announcer] Made with real cream.
Reddi Whip, instant greatification.
(audience applauds)
- We're back with the stars
of "The Neighborhood",
Cedric The Entertainer and Tichina Arnold.
Now we want to have a
little Valentine's Day fun
with the two of you, so
we're going to find out
how much America's favorite new TV couple
really knows about each
other in a game we're calling
Husband and Wife but Not in Real Life.
(cheering)
(clapping)
Before the show, we
asked Tichina and Cedric
a few questions about themselves,
and now it's time to see if they can guess
how the other person answered.
If they can get three matches,
everyone in our studio audience
goes home with a prize.
Are you ready?
(audience cheers)
Pressure's on.
(Cedric coughing)
- No whispering answers, no whispering.
- [Cedric] John David?
First person, okay Cedric.
- [Tichina] I'm nervous.
- Who is Tichina's
favorite musical artist?
- Oh wow, I'm going to say,
I'm going, Aretha Franklin.
- Tichina, is he right?
- Close baby close.
(buzzer buzzes)
- Very close, okay Sharon, you're up.
- Okay, who is...
now you guys come on.
- [Sara] You gotta move it along
or you won't get any right.
- Who is Cedric's celebrity crush.
- Oh yeah.
- I'm gonna go with Rihanna.
- Is that right?
Rihanna she's young still
but she's still woman,
and she's just awesomely talented.
- [Sara] Cedric, let's see the answer.
- I said...
(buzzer buzzes)
- [Sara] Carrie Anne, you're up.
- You guys better pull it together here.
Cedric your turn.
Cedric, focus.
Who is Tichina's celebrity crush?
- Cedric The Entertainer.
(audience laughs)
- [Sara] Final answer,
is he right Tichina?
- No, he ain't right.
(buzzer buzzes)
- John David Washington,
Denzel's son, right?
- [Sara] Okay, now we got Sheryl.
- Tichina, what movie
always makes Cedric cry?
- I wanna say "The Five Heartbeats".
- [Sara] Is she correct Cedric?
I'm guessing she's not
based on her track record.
(buzzer buzzes)
- We've got another question.
- So, Cedric, what is
Tichina's biggest fear?
- Imma go with bugs,
maybe bugs or something.
- [Sara] Bugs, is he right?
- You are so right.
(audience cheers)
- Sharon, let's do one
more question quickly here.
- All right, which celebrity
does Cedric text the most?
- Oh this is a no-brainer, Steve Harvey.
(audience cheers)
- Cedric, is she right?
Let's see it Cedric, we gotta go to break.
- I was going to say George
Lopez, but Steve first.
(audience gasps)
- Guys, you only got one match.
Thank God you're not married in real life,
but we don't want anyone
to leave empty-handed,
so everyone in our studio audience
is being treated to something
special for Valentine's Day.
(audience cheers)
Hotel Via in San Francisco,
a three-day, two-night stay
for you and your Valentine.
Hotel Via is a boutique
hotel in San Francisco
with a stunning rooftop lounge.
It features 159 chic and
sophisticated guestrooms
which boasts a modern
minimalist design concept.
Visit HotelViaSF.com.
This getaway value retails for $950,
for your chance to win at home
go to thetalk.com/giveaways.
Tichina Arnold and Cedric
The Entertainer, thank you.
"The Neighborhood" airs
Friday nights at eight on CBS
and will be right back.
- It's Friday.
- So let your hair down.
- I don't look the same every day.
- The Talk, on CBS.
- [Announcer] If you, like
many people, are covered
by both Medicare and
your state's Medicaid,
here's something important to know.
Now you can get even more health benefits
than you already have.
It's the UnitedHealthcare
Dual Complete plan.
To find out if you or
someone you care about
is eligible, it's easy.
Call now to talk with us.
We can explain it all
and answer any questions.
Medicaid gives you benefits,
and Medicare gives you some too
but a Dual Complete plan can add even more
benefits and features
compared to original Medicare.
You'll have lots of doctors
and hospitals to chose from,
plus prescription drug coverage,
and depending on where you live,
you can enjoy other benefits too.
Like dental care, vision coverage,
and rides to and from
your doctor or hospital.
You can even get a health products catalog
with credits you can use
to shop for everyday things
like vitamins, oral health
items, and first aid kids.
And best of all, with this plan,
there is no additional cost to you.
Remember, if you have
Medicare and Medicaid,
chances are you can get
a Dual Complete plan.
So call now to talk
with us and learn more.
Or ask to have a licensed
agent visit your home
and take you through
everything step by step.
We know healthcare can be confusing.
UnitedHealthcare can
straighten things out.
With 40 years of experience,
you can count on us
to be there all along the way.
With a Dual Complete plan,
you can have a wide choice
of doctors to choose from,
better prescription drug coverage,
dental and vision coverage too.
All at no additional cost.
You have Medicare, you have Medicaid.
You may be eligible for Dual Complete.
So call the number on your screen now
to see if you're eligible
or to enroll in a Dual Complete
plan from UnitedHealthcare.
♪ So soft ♪
- Charmin Ultra Soft.
- It's softer than ever.
- [Announcer] Charmin Ultra
Soft is softer than ever,
so it's harder to resist.
(record scratching)
- Okay, this is getting a little weird.
- Enjoy the go, with Charmin.
- I got a certain way I like to do things.
I like Consumer Cellular.
I get unlimited talk and
text for just $25 a month.
With no contract.
They received a J.D, power award
for highest customer service again.
- And Consumer Cellular has
been an approved AARP provider
since 2008, so we trust them.
Reliable nationwide
coverage for way less money,
that's the way...
- We like it.
- Get wireless the way you like it.
Call, go online, or find us at Target.
- Oh milk, am I willing to
pay the price for loving you?
You'll make my morning but ruin my day.
- Complicated relationship with milk?
- Pour on the Lactaid.
100% real milk, just without
that annoying lactose.
- Mmm, that's good.
- Has MacGuyver met his match?
- MacGuyver!
- She's intense.
- You're just figuring that out?
- Then, FBI's most wanted
fugitive is in Five-0's custody.
- He's gone.
- Let's just let him die in the storm.
- That would be too good for this guy.
- A new Hawaii Five-0, after
a new Macguyver, CBS Friday.
- [Female Announcer] Great
guests, big giveaways.
You haven't seen The Talk
until you've seen it in person.
- Thank you guys so much for being here.
You've been a spectacular audience.
- Go to TheTalk.com for
tickets and join the fun.
(audience cheers)
- We can't say goodbye on Valentine's Day
without giving you one more present.
It's time to bring you
something we think you'll love
in today's Must Have.
(audience cheers)
Kate Spade New York In
Full Bloom Eau de Parfum
is a modern rose floral
scent with a fresh twist,
perfect for Valentine's Day gifting.
Everyone in today's studio
audience is going home
with a Kate Spade New York
In Full Bloom fragrance.
(audience cheers)
For your chance to win at home
retweet our post on Twitter
or go to thetalk.com/giveaways.
Thank you all for
joining us, and remember,
it's always the right time to have...
- [Audience] The Talk!
(audience claps in unison)
- [Announcer] Don't miss a
new S.W.A.T., CBS tonight.
- [Announcer] Next ET,
Blake, Gwen, and Elvis?
- It's about the only trick I got.
- [Announcer] We've got the
couple's connection to The King
plus Harry and Meghan's first
married Valentine's Day apart?
Next ET.
- [Announcer] Tonight at
seven thirty on WUSA9.
- Can you really sell a
house in any condition?
Call us to answer a few questions.
Meet us at your house to
go over the paperwork.
Pick a convenient closing date, that's it.
♪ Express Home Buyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
- After your car accident,
is the insurance company
pressuring you to settle?
- When you need help dealing
with an insurance company
after a car accident, you have a lawyer.
- That's right, when you need
a lawyer, you have a lawyer.
No matter what kind of
accident you've been in,
call us at Saiontz and Kirk,
or go to YouHaveALawyer.com.
- When you've been hurt,
and you need a lawyer.
- You have a lawyer.
- 1-800-Lawyers or YouHaveALawyer.com
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-Lawyers
or visit YouHaveALawyer.com.
If you have a phone, you have a lawyer.
- An inherited house can
be a blessing or a burden.
If you're feeling more burden,
call Express Home Buyers
and sell that house in less time
than it will take to clean it.
♪ Express Home Buyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
♪ The one and only TV nine ♪
- [Female Announcer]
This is Daily Blast Live.
We're talking to about...