♪ In seven days ♪
(light music)
- Welcome back in to Wake Up Washington.
The record-breaking film, Black Panther,
is the first superhero movie ever
to be nominated for best picture.
It features a predominately
Black cast, and gives Black boys
and girls a chance to imagine
themselves as superheroes.
Well, Black Panther is also
an example of Afrofuturism.
The cultural movement has long been part
of African-American arts.
Alex Wagner explains
its history and revival
as we celebrate Black History Month.
- I see these tweets at
times where people are like,
I just wanna see Black mermaids
and Black people in space.
I wanna see Black stories
that aren't about Black pain
because the pain is constant.
- [Alex] At just 25 years old,
Nigerian-American writer, Tomi Adeyemi,
is among the artists at the forefront
of the resurgence of Afrofuturism.
- It's just kind of like a
utopia to imagine what if.
Like, what if this story wasn't a story
of having everything taken away
and having so much, like,
oppression, and brutality
and senseless murder, and slavery,
like, what if it could be
something completely different?
- That's the foundation of the best seller
Children of Blood and Bone,
a West-African fantasy novel
featuring a young Black
female protagonist.
When did it occur to
you that women of color
men of color, children of color
could be fantasy characters?
- I didn't realize until my
senior year of high school
that no characters look like me,
so all of my protagonists were
White or they were biracial.
Then I realized it's not
just me who needs this,
it's like, it's other
people who look like me,
but it's also people
who don't look like me
because the reason I didn't think
I could be in a story was
'cause I didn't see it.
- [Alex] Through her
writing, she also directly
tackles racism and inequality.
- [Tomi] I wanted to write a story
that commented on the Black experience.
- In some ways, Afrofuturism is inherently
kind of a revolutionary act.
- Yeah.
- Do you think of yourself
as a revolutionary?
- At this point I can think of myself
as a part of the revolution.
- [Alex] And so does Grammy
Nominee, Janelle Monae.
♪ Oh me, oh me, oh me, oh my ♪
On her new album, Dirty Computer,
Monae explores Afrofuturism through music.
- Afrofuturism is about Black people,
us seeing ourselves in the future.
Knowing that we are not the stereotypes
that have been perpetuated on us.
♪ I am not America's nightmare ♪
- [Alex] Monae believes this is the time
for Afrocentric art.
- It's a way for Black women like myself
to tell our stories through our own lens
because I think it's important
that we're telling our stories,
because if we allow other
people who are not us
to tell our stories, they
may not be told properly.
- [Black Panther] The revolution.
- [Alex] Enter Black Panther.
With a Black superhero and
a nearly all Black cast
set in an African-inspired
utopia sometime in the future--
- We are home.
- [Alex] Panther popularized
the idea of Afrofuturism,
but its roots run deep.
- All the early abolitionists
that we celebrate,
the Frederick Douglass's,
the Sojourner Truth's,
were all Afrofuturists, Harriet Tubman,
Sun Ra, George Clinton.
- [Alex] Cultural critic,
Greg Tate, is considered
one the leading scholars of this movement.
- Anybody who
had a vision
of the Black people's story
and presence and imaging,
can be told and elevated.
- On one hand we have a
movie like Black Panther,
which is a lot of people's
entry point for Afrofuturism,
but you also have Black
Lives Matter movement,
right?
- Right.
- [Alex] Do you see a connection
between those two things?
- Oh, definitely, I mean, I don't think
that Black Panther would have happened
without the precedent
of Black Lives Matter
'cause I think that
anytime there's outrage
and protest in the streets,
the cultural elites in America
tend to open up resources
and opportunity and space
for, you know, for Black creatives.
- [Alex] And the response suggests
audiences will start to see
even more Afrofuturist art.
- Black Panther!
(audience cheering)
Yes!
- [Alex] Black Panther snagged
the top prize at the SAG Awards,
is nominated for seven Oscars--
- You get to decide.
- And a sequel is underway.
Tomi Adeyemi's book is being made into
a major motion picture, with
two more books in the works.
Do you think arts and
entertainment are changing?
- I definitely think they're changing.
We're finally getting
people who want to share it
with people, and people
who don't think that,
oh, people aren't gonna relate
to this because it's Black,
or they're not gonna relate to this
because it's African, it's too different.
They're like, no this is a great story
with great characters,
so let's make it visible,
and when people find it,
they'll fall in love with it.
- Gotta say, I'm pretty
happy to see the direction
that arts and entertainment
is headed into now.
It just seems more inclusive,
and yes, films like that,
you have little boys and
little girls, you know,
who say, hey, you know,
I see myself there.
- And I can be anything I
want, I can be a superhero.
I can conquer whatever I want.
I'm excited to see how Black
Panther does at the Oscars.
- Oh yeah, tonight, oh yeah,
I know it's gonna sweep up
a lot of the awards there.
- It's gonna be the talk of
the town tomorrow morning.
- Yeah, for sure.
- Yeah.
- All right, talk of the town
around here is your forecast,
it's gonna be nice.
- A little bumpy ride, we
got the showers moving out.
It's turning warmer
today, but it is windy.
So those gusty winds could
bring down trees and power lines
between today, tonight
and tomorrow morning.
That's when we'll see
winds gusting in the metro
as high as 50 miles per hour,
higher than that out in the mountains.
We'll see a pretty quiet week overall,
more showers at the end of the week,
but today it's all about
the wind and the warmth.
- That's right, so take it easy out there.
Enjoy your Sunday.
(light music)
That does it for Wake Up Washington.
CBS Sunday Morning is coming up next.
- Have a great day!
- [WUSA Announcer] You've
been watching WUSA 9 News,
with a weather forecast
rated most accurate
for the last seven years.
(light music)
- [Verify Announcer] Somehow,
somewhere along the line,
the world changed.
We lost something that seemed so simple,
something we always took for granted,
the ability to know what's real.
(audience clapping)
- Great performance.
(upbeat music)
- [Verify Announcer] It's harder then ever
to separate fact from fiction,
so Verify is working harder
than ever to change that.
It's time for the world
to once again say, I know.
- Yes.
- [Verify Announcer] Verify.
Look into it.
(exhilarating music)
- [Honda Announcer] It's the Honda
Presidents' Day sales
event, and it's your chance
to get a new Honda vehicle that can pack
all of life's best adventures.
Yep, time to start checking
off that bucket list.
Selfies over at Niagara Falls?
Check.
Gateway Arch?
Being awarded by kbb.com as
2018's best overall brand?
Check.
So pop into your Honda dealer today
for great deals on some of
our most popular vehicles
at the Honda Presidents' Day sales event.
(upbeat music)
- [Mattress Firm Announcer]
The Presidents' Day Sale
at Mattress Firm has been
extended by popular demand.
That means it's your last chance
to take home a free adjustable base
with your qualifying mattress purchase.
Up to a $699 value, absolutely free.
See what customers like Brecken
in Maryland are raving about.
Plus, throughout the store,
save up to $500 on mattresses,
like a Serta memory foam
queen mattress, now only $397.
Hurry in, these deals end Tuesday!
Your budget stretches
further at Mattress Firm.
(upbeat guitar music)
- [Announcer] We may not
all be in the same boat,
but out on the water, we're
all on the same wavelength.
In the Florida Keys and Key West.
- Here's your Buick, Sir.
- Actually, that's my Buick.
(upbeat music)
- Your Buick doesn't have a roof rack.
- This is my Buick.
- How are we gonna fit
in your Mom's Buick?
- Easy.
- I like that new Buick.
- Me too.
- I was actually talking about that Buick.
- I knew that.
- Did you?
- [Buick Announcer]
Buick's fresh new lineup
is full of surprises.
Get great deals on our
expectation-shattering lineup.
Pay no interest for 72
months on most Buick models.
(exhilarating music)
(trumpet music)