- Instances removed,
and they don't have
that privilege anymore,
they're extremely upset.
They have to rely on friends
and neighbors and family.
Families for rides.
But I would say, as sheriff,
my number one priority
is keeping the road safe.
(typing)
- [Berkeley] I wanted to know
how many reports are filed every year?
How many drivers lose their license,
and why does one person get a road test,
like Rosalee, and another driver doesn't?
The State DMV would not answer
those specific questions,
but wrote in an email, quote,
"The thorough review process
allows a driver to demonstrate
"their fitness to drive and
helps the DMV ensure safety
"on New York's roadways
for all who use them,
"which is our top priority".
How has this impacted your life?
- I need to be independent.
And I've always been independent.
What can I say?
- Berkeley Brean, News 10, NBC.
- More plans were announced today
for Skyview on the Ridge,
the redevelopment of the
former Irondequoit Mall.
St. Ann's community will expand
their adult day care health
service there in 2020.
They provide care for older adults
and people with disabilities.
St. Ann's says there is a growing need
for adult day health care
services in our community.
And the new location will double
the number of people that can be served.
- [Reporter] Now, your
First Alert forecast
with meteorologist Robert Speta,
featuring Rochester's
only live local radar,
First Alert Doppler 10,
powered by AP Plumbing.
- A rather nice evening
out here in Rochester.
This is overlooking the Genesee River
there in Charlotte.
We're still looking at nice weather
through the rest of the week.
It will start to warm up
by the end of the week,
and even become a little bit more muggy,
with rain returning by
Sunday night, into Monday.
But here's the key thing,
over the next few days,
there is nothing severe in the forecast,
and even into the weekend as well.
I got green across the board here
on that News 10 NBC threat tracker.
But right now, any rain
we had earlier on today,
it's been pushed towards the south,
thanks to the lake breeze,
keeping things pretty
clear through tonight.
60 degrees for our low,
it's gonna be a pleasant
night in the forecast.
Heading through tomorrow,
we're gonna be looking
at those temperatures
warming up to about 78 to 82 degrees,
with mostly sunny skies by 5:00 p.m.
By the way, that is Remo, or Rehmo,
I hope I'm saying it right,
I'm gonna say both of 'em.
He a nice dog, he's ready
to go for a ride there,
on the dog walking forecast.
Always do remember these images
are sent in by that WHEC weather app.
All right, let's take a look
at those temperatures across the board
for the high tomorrow.
A little bit cooler near the lake shore,
we got 79 in Irondequoit,
74 only in Sodus.
Meanwhile, in the Canandaigua
could be upwards of
about 80 degrees for your high.
You got the Ontario County
Fair going on there.
80 in Geneva, and Dansville
about 77 for your high.
You have that chance of an isolated shower
by the afternoon,
down into the Finger Lakes as well.
Be very, very local,
because this high area of high pressure
is finally gonna drift towards the East,
and really just dominate,
starting on Thursday and Friday,
and also into Saturday.
And the more it dominates,
the less likely we have of
scattered showers out there.
So Thursday, there is a small chance.
But then eventually by
Friday into Saturday,
this just comes on overhead.
I know this is picking up on rain,
but I don't have it on the forecast.
I think this is gonna be
suppressing it too much,
but eventually this front
is gonna work its way in by
Sunday night into Monday.
The high is gonna move out of the way,
and that influence from it
is gonna be going to the wayside,
and of course, that means
increase in rainfall,
as we go ahead into the
early part of next week.
Especially Tuesday.
Tuesday is looking like a messy one.
83, maybe even with a chance
for thunderstorm with that.
And Wednesday we're also looking
at some rainfall, as well.
But before that happens, boy oh boy,
this week, this week's looking brilliant.
I mean Thursday, Friday and Saturday,
all of the sunshine.
I think the only thing I could say
that you need to worry
about is the UV index.
You definitely wanna be aware of that,
get that sunblock ready to
go as the sun just comes out.
- Always
- Yeah, yeah, especially
this time of year.
- Yeah, right.
All right, Robert, thank you.
Well, it's a sign that football season
is almost here.
What you need to know about
the Buffalo Bills training camp,
if you plan on going.
Plus, which local county is opting out
of making you pay a tax for
paper bags at the grocery store.
But first, here's a look
at what we're working on
from News 10 NBC at 11.
The Rochester area is
experiencing a craft beer boom.
So where do our brewers
get their ingredients?
Turns out a local hop
farm is a major supplier.
In our small business spotlight,
we take you to Cobblestone Hop Yard.
That's tonight, at 11.