- [Lesli] It's nearly at our doorstep.
Topper what's the latest?
- We're just hours from snow breaking out
across the metro area, in fact,
we're about 12 hours
from snow in the metro.
So let's go over the
snow fall totals again,
these are little bit lower
than we showed you yesterday,
doesn't mean the roads will be any better.
Three to five inches
Leesburg, Gaithersburg,
Frederick, Martinsburg,
and points north and west.
And yes, you could exceed
that three to five inch mark.
One to three in the immediate metro area,
DC, Rockville, Bethesda, Fairfax, Bowie,
and even down into Waldorf.
And in extreme southern Maryland,
we're just talkin' about a trace to one.
That hasn't changed that much,
you just don't have the cold air in place
long enough to sustain that much snow.
Or that much sleet for that matter.
So, what about the models?
Have they come into my way of thinking?
For the most part they have,
still four and a half for the RPM.
All the rest of the models
are under three inches,
so I think they've finally got a handle
on just how much sleet is
gonna fall with the snow.
So once again, moderate to
heavy snow, 6:00 am to noon.
Roads will be dangerous, period.
It will accumulate very
quickly and once it starts
it will pick up intensity very quickly.
Snow will turn to a mix, north
and west in the afternoon.
It will turn to rain DC south
and east in the afternoon.
Some of that rain can be heavy overnight,
everybody goes to rain overnight
and then morning showers on Thursday
and then we are in the 50s.
No shortage of moisture.
This is a tremendous storm,
stretching already from Cape
Hatteras back to Kansas city.
Even all the way back to Iowa.
So, here's the timing.
5:00 am, snow on our doorstep,
but snowed already a
couple hours in Culpeper,
snowing already in Manassas.
By 7:00, snowin' across the metro area,
even in Prince George's
county up into Baltimore.
By 10:00 we still have snow
beginning to mix down into the south.
I think this mile's little
slow in eroding the cold air.
Still has snow by 1:00,
I think we're gonna go probably
to a mix in DC by noon,
with the snow hanging on north
up toward Frederick and I-70.
Then by 4:00, just rain in the DC area,
but still hanging onto
some ice north and west.
We'll come back, we'll
talk about the potential
for an ice storm north or west of town
when the snow transitions
from snow to freezing rain.
- Thanks Topper.
Preparations underway all across the DMV
for the winter storm.
Late tonight, salt and plow trucks
will be standing by at the ready.
Peggy Fox, she joins us from
VDOT's massive operation.
- [Peggy] Don't let these blooming pansies
or daffodils pushing up fool you.
Late February snow
storms can pack a punch,
with huge snowfalls.
Are you ready for the snow?
- No.
- [Peggy] Ready or not, it's coming.
Hardware stores have stocked
up on shovels and sleds.
- Whole new bunch, ready to rock and roll.
- And in Virginia,
VDOT has already started treating roads.
You see those streaks on the road?
They're from brine, put down overnight.
This was one of VDOT's 18 facilities
across northern Virginia.
It looks empty now, but come midnight,
it's gonna be rockin'.
A continuous line of plow trucks
will fill up from the salt dome
to treat major roads.
Sand will then be used in neighborhoods.
VDOT's Ellen Kamilakis says
they'll have 3,000 trucks
covering 14,000 miles of roads.
- Most of our fleet is a contract fleet.
So these trucks are
either landscaping trucks,
they're construction trucks by day.
When they go from Clark
Kent to being Superman
and they become our plow trucks at night.
- [Peggy] Each truck needs a spreader.
- The spreader goes in
and is attached in there
and then they get a load of salt
and they drive off and as they drive
and the unit spins in the back,
it spreads salt evenly on the road.
- Now, of course the trucks
don't plow right away.
They wait for a signal.
As soon as snow gets two inches high,
VDOT puts out the call, plows down,
and then things get exciting.
- What we're asking for this is
for people to stay off
the roads on Wednesday.
With the amount of snow
that we're gonna be getting
and with the rate in which
it's gonna be falling,
we're concerned with that,
especially during rush hour.
- [Peggy] Stay home if you can.
In Fairfax County, Peggy Fox, WUSA9.
- [Bruce] And a reminder,
because of the wintery
weather we're expecting,
the Wake Up Washington
team will be on early,
4:00 in the morning we're talking,
with the latest on conditions
and closings because of the storm.
- I'm Bernie Sanders.
I'm running for President.
- [Lesli] Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders
made it official today.
He's joining a crowded field competing for
the democratic nomination for President.
Sanders is the 10th candidate who wants
to challenge President
Trump in the 2020 election.
In an interview with CBS This
Morning's John Dickerson,
the 77 year old progressive says,
he's okay if people call him a radical.
- I believe that people
are inherently entitled to healthcare.
I believe people are entitled to get
the best education they can.
- [Lesli] The Trump administration reacted
to the announcement by Sanders saying,
"The American people will reject
"an agenda of sky high taxes,
government run health care,
"and coddling dictators
like those in Venezuela."
Sanders says he does not want
the US to become Venezuela
and hopes Americans do
not believe too much
of what the President has to say.
- Legal challenges are now
mounting to President Trump
and his declaration of
a national emergency
to fully fund that border wall.
Natalie Brand breaks
down the legal arguments
against the President's move.
- [Natalie] President Trump is defending
his national emergency declaration
to build a southern border wall.
- I have an absolute right
to call national security,
we need strong borders.
We have to stop drugs
and crime and criminals.
- [Natalie] But Professor
Louis Michael Seidman
of Georgetown University
says the statistics
may not be in the President's favor,
as his declaration faces
multiple legal challenges.
- Border crossings are way down
from where they were several years ago.
Most of the drugs that the
President worries about
come through ports of entry.
- 16 states, including California,
are suing President Trump.
Arguing that he does not have
the constitutional authority
to declare the emergency.
A separate lawsuit from
some members of Congress
could also be coming
on those same grounds.
- Congress has pretty
much expressly decided
not to spend this money.
- [Natalie] Much of that money
will come from the
Defense Department budget.
Officials say DHS is already looking
at construction locations.
- We know there'll be
a large portion of it
being built in the Rio Grande Valley.
- [Natalie] Which sets
up another legal battle
with Texas landowners,
three of whom have already filed suit
over possible land seizures.
- Those people, more clearly
maybe than anyone else,
have standing to object to
what the President has done.
- [Natalie] Like the President
and most legal experts,
Professor Seidman expects
the Supreme Court will
ultimately decide the issue.
Natalie Brand, CBS News, the White House.
- A new NPR PBS news hour
poll shows that, overall,
a majority of Americans
disapprove of the President's use
of a national emergency to build the wall.
- [Lesli] We're following
some breaking news
out of south east DC, it's
been a violent afternoon there.
A teenager has been shot.
It happened along the 2600
block of Stanton Road.
DC police tell us that boy
was conscious and breathing
when first responders
rushed him to the hospital.
We don't know what led up to the shooting.
Police say they're looking for a suspect
wearing a blue hoodie and tan khaki pants,
last seen headed toward Douglas Road.
About 20 minutes from
there, earlier today,
a crime alert about another crime.
Three people, including a child,
were shot in that instance.
Eli Place, near the Fort Dupont ice arena.
Bullet casings could be
seen littering the street,
along with a Lexus sedan that
had it's windows shot out.
Police say all but one of the victims
was conscious and breathing
when they were taken to the hospital.
We don't know anything about a motive
or suspects in that attack.
- [Bruce] There's an important
meeting at Winston Churchill
Senior High School in Potomac tonight.
Parents of the Montgomery County school
are invited to discuss an event
where students handed out passes
granting others permission
to use the N word.
And there's more.
School officials say they'll
also address a swastika
that was drawn on a
desk earlier this year.
The meeting is said to
begin at 7:00 tonight
at Churchill High School auditorium.
Coming up, Frederick County mom
detained by immigration officers
talks about her nightmare
and her long awaited
reunion with her family.
- [Lesli] Plus, Vatican secrets.
Despite their vow of celibacy,
the catholic church has guidelines
for priests who father children.
The news continues after this.
- Track the winter weather with me
and search for the WUSA9
app in your app store!
- [Announcer] Tonight.
- What do we got?
- [Announcer] NCIS has a surprise so good,
missing it would be criminal.
- Your computer is tryin to--
- Take down the Department of Defense.
- [Announcer] New NCIS, then.
- Looks like a professional hit.
- [Announcer] The search for answers,
leads to more questions.
- Who hired you?
- [Announcer] A new FBI, after a new NCIS.
CBS Tonight.
Tonight.
- If you get this, send help!
(gunshot)
- [Announcer] One journalist under siege.
One conspiracy uncovered.
- We got nothin' to go on.
- [Announcer] NCIS New Orleans, tonight.
(wind blowing)
- [Narrator] When winter
rears it's ugly head,
you can stay in and cozy up to the fire.
Or, go out
and light one.
(suspenseful music)
Dodge Durango.
Join the brotherhood of muscle
and hurry in for winter deals.
Now, get $500 President's Day bonus cash
for a total cash allowance of $2,000
on the 2019 Dodge Durango
SXT all wheel drive.
(suspenseful music)
It's time to go Toyota.
Go connected, with a sporty Camry,
with the latest tech.
Compatible with your
favorite apps and wifi.
Now, lease a Camry for $219 a month,
or buy with $1,500 cash back.
Or go with a stylish Corolla
and lease for just $199 a month
or buy with $1,500 cash back
and two years of no cost
maintenance included.
Go see your Toyota dealer today!
Toyota, let's go places.
- A Jewish cemetery was
found desecrated today
in eastern France.
Swastika's and inscriptions were found
on some 80 graves in a village
located close to Strasbourg.
This comes two months after
another Jewish cemetery
was vandalized and on the day
that France held a
large gathering in Paris
to protest antisemitism.
French President, Emmanuel
Macron, also visited
the Holocaust Memorial today in the city.
- [Bruce] CBS news has
confirmed the Vatican
has kept secret guidelines for priests
who father children.
For nearly nine centuries
the catholic church
has forbidden it's priests
from having sex or getting married.
Sarah Thomas says she's proof
that priests sometimes break those vows.
She says her mother was told by the church
to keep her birth a secret.
Thomas first met her father, a priest,
in England when she was 14 years old.
- It soon became apparent
that he couldn't,
or wouldn't, and wasn't allowed
to be any sort of father to me.
- What was the hardest part
about all of this growing up?
- Feeling very isolated.
I literally thought I
was the only priest child
in the world.
- [Bruce] The Catholic church in Ireland
published ground breaking guidelines
for priests who fathered children.
Church officials in
America are now looking
at a similar model.
This week, Pope Francis
meeting in Rome with Bishops
to discuss this issue
and the sexual abuse scandals
that have plagued the church
on several continents.
Coming up at 7:00 Off Script tonight,
I've got an exclusive interview
with a priest and church scholar
who is heading to that meeting in Rome.
- [Lesli] Coming up, Manny
Machado has a new team now.
How will that impact Bryce Harper?
Darren Haynes has more
from Nat's Spring
Training camp in Florida.
- [Bruce] Your health
matters to us here at WUSA9,
that's why we're holding
free health screenings
from noon until 7:00 this Thursday,
February 21st at the
Kentland Community Center
on Pinebrook Avenue in Landover.
Our initiative is called
Impact Health Matters.
- [Lesli] We're partnering
with UM Capitol Region Health
and the Prince George's
County Health Department
to provide all sorts of
screenings and demos,
about 20 of them,
and a few of them are on
your screen right now.
Cholesterol, glucose, dental screenings.
We'll have doctors on hand
to answer your questions
and you can even give
back to the community
by donating blood.
- [Bruce] While screenings are free,
you do need to register for some of them,
as well as the blood drive, ahead of time.
You can do this by going
to WUSA9.com/HealthMatters.
Again, that's WUSA9.com/HealthMatters.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Next ET, Miranda's
wedding secrets unveiled.
Plus, Meghan's baby shower in New York.
And...
- I'm exclusively in London
with Victoria Beckham.
- [Announcer] Next ET.
- [Female Announcer]
Tonight at 7:30 on WUSA9.
- [Male Announcer] Fourth
of July has its fireworks.
Christmas, gifts.
But what about Presidents' Day?
Let's just say the voters
will be very happy.
Announcing our best offers
on America's best selling brand.
You gotta love democracy.
Through February 28th only,
get $4,000 total cash on select Ford SUVs.
Hurry to your local Ford dealers
for best selection during the
President's Day Sales Event.
- [Female Announcer]
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart
and restoring a father's faith.
It's standing tall after one surgery,
not six.
Stronger is being a typical kid
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding it earlier
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is seeking answers
and not giving up
until you find them.
Because we don't just
want your kids to grow up,
we want them to grow up stronger.
- Ready to go when you are.
- Wow, you look nice!
Getting around isn't as
easy as it used to be.
That's why we called Bath Fitter.
They removed our old tub
and installed a beautiful
new spacious shower.
Now getting in and out is a breeze.
And we have peace of mind
with seamless walls that
provide a water-tight fit.
Plus their lifetime guarantee.
Thanks to Bath Fitter
Life is so much easier
with a shower we love.
- [Announcer] Call today
for this month's offer.
- Wimpy trash bags?
C'mon!
Hefty, Hefty, Hefty!
(crash)
- Hey ladies.
Buy Hefty Ultra Stronger.
A low price.
- Dada.
(soft impact)
- I wish.
- [Announcer] Get Hefty Ultra Stronger.
Costs less than Glad Forceflex
where sold head to head.
- Mmmm, yummy lip balm!
- Yummy lip balm?
My lips get so dry and cracked
I need serious relief.
That's why I use O'Keeffe's Lip Repair.
It's all day moisture in one use
and is guaranteed relief for
extremely dry, cracked lips.
Thanks to O'Keeffe's
I got my lips back.
- This President's Day there's big news
at Nissan Now!
No brand received more J.D.
Power Initial Quality Awards
for cars and trucks than Nissan.
That means that people
love their new Nissans.
So we're thanking you
with big savings on our lineup.
Including Rogue,
with ProPILOT Assist.
- [Announcer] For a limited time
save up to $3,500 on the 2019 Rogue
or the 2019 Sentra.
- Get to Nissan now
before these offers are yesterday's news.
(rock music)
- A Frederick County mom
and local civil rights leader
at the center of an immigration battle
is reunited with her kids.
Roxana Santos broke down today
as she talked about the terror
of being detained by
ICE for nearly a month
despite a federal judge's order
blocking her deportation.
Here's Scott Broom.
(speaking in a foreign language)
- [Scott] Roxana Santos,
speaking in Spanish,
said she's now living in terror
that she could be taken
from her four kids again
at any moment.
The three youngest,
including six year old twins,
are U.S. citizens.
- [Roxana's Son] I'm
happy to be with my mom.
(speaking in foreign language)
- [Translator] "I'm really scared
"that they could separate
me from my children again."
- [Scott] Santos was taken by ICE,
locked up in a rural county jail,
and threatened with
deportation in January,
sparking protest.
(protestors chant)
- [Scott] She just won a civil rights suit
against the Frederick
County sheriff's department
for illegally profiling her,
leading to an unjustified arrest in 2007.
The final stage of that
case is still in court,
the reason a judge blocked
her deportation for now.
Nick Katzs is Santos' lawyer.
- Immigration has no priorities anymore.
They're going after mothers,
they're going after young people.
We need to protect them
and make sure that they're comfortable
interacting with the local police
and that that's not a
pipeline to deportation.
- Santos may have U.S. citizen kids,
but the fact is she did
illegally immigrate 14 years ago
to flee violence in El Salvador.
Which means ICE is within its rights
to attempt to separate the family again.
In Hyattsville, Scott Broom, WUSA9.
- All right, so a lot of schools,
are already calling it now.
- And for good reason.
I mean, the roads are going
to be a mess tomorrow.
Between 6:00 am and noon
that's gonna be the big shot of snow,
and the heaviest snow,
and it's gonna accumulate quickly.
We talked about this yesterday.
When it starts to snow
it will become moderate
to heavy very soon,
and it will accumulate
very quickly as well.
So here we go.
Three to five.
Leesburg, Gaithersburg,
just north of Rockville,
and just kinda touching
parts of Fairfax County
and northern Prince William County.
And notice the plus sign.
Yeah, there are spots that could get
more than five inches in that.
In the metro area, one to three inches.
We may end up with two inches of snow
and an inch of sleet inside the belt way.
So that includes Bethesda,
Chevy Chase, DC, Bowie,
down to Waldorf, and even Fredericksburg.
Down to the south of Fredericksburg,
across into the southern Maryland area,
we have a trace to just an inch.
Not a huge problem there.
But if you're traveling,
you're gonna try to come up
through southern Maryland,
up five or 301, once you
get into Charles County,
if you're doing it in the morning,
it will be bad.
Snow fall.
Here we go.
2.8, 2.4.
I think the computers have kinda come into
our way of thinking,
which is good.
Makes me feels a little
bit more confident.
All right, so here we go.
Tremendous amount of moisture.
Most of this is rain,
little bit of snow popping up here
in northwestern North
Carolina, in the mountains.
And this is on schedule for us to be here
either side of 6:00 tomorrow.
So, on the Bread-O-Meter.
Well, I like doin' a pure
snow on the Bread-O-Meter,
but because it's gonna
be a impactful storm,
and disruptive,
we're gonna make it a five.
So we're gonna call it a legitimate storm.
Between the snow and the ice.
And I think it will be
plowable and sledable.
Now, as it goes to ice,
power outages, I think
unlikely in the metro,
but out toward I-81,
isolated power outages, okay?
And then further west,
Hagerstown into Cumberland,
kinda where you had the
ice about a week ago,
we could see power outages there.
We're a little bit more concerned
about power outages there.
And here's why.
This model has very little ice
around the metro,
and it has okay amounts,
it could probably handle
2/10 of Petersburg
and 2/10 of Romney.
But this model's way aggressive
and it has almost an inch
in Cumberland to Oakland.
And even more in our burgs.
0.3 in Leesburg and Gaitersburg.
That would lead to some blims coming down
and some power outages.
So, let's talk about types of precip.
So it's snow if everything is cold,
and we start out that way,
but it doesn't stay that way.
It ends up we get this little warm wedge
and that turns things to sleet.
That's what bounces.
And worst of all, if we
it turn to freezing rain
that falls liquid and freezes on contact.
That's the worse case scenario.
So, roads worse 6:00 am to noon.
It will kick to a mix
and then rain overnight.
And then morning showers,
we're in the 50s by Thursday.
So, 33 snow at 6:00 am,
moderate to heavy snow at 9:00,
and then things begin
to change a little bit
into a mix.
So, red weather alert tomorrow 32,
56 on Thursday.
Look at Friday, what a
way to finish the week!
Sunshine and--
(poppy sound effect drowns out weatherman)
Little bit of a blip of Saturday,
chilly with rain.
And then 66 on Sunday.
Upper 40s Monday and Tuesday.
Lesli.
- [Lesli] All right, four
wedding anniversaries,
birthdays and countless
holidays have passed
since Ken Gemmell and his
little girl, Arabelle,
lost their family.
It was two weeks before Christmas in 2014,
a plane crashed into
their Gaitersburg house.
And inside was Marie.
She was home on maternity leave.
She was found cradling her sons,
seven week old Devon,
and three year old Cole,
in an upstairs bathroom.
But instead of letting
this tragedy destroy them,
Ken and Arabelle are fulfilling a dream
to honor Marie, Devon, and Cole.
They wanna rebuild this playground,
and you can help.
To learn how, go to WUSA9,
our mobile app or our website,
and then tonight at 11:00
hear about the design plans
little Arabelle has to honor
her mother and little brothers.
We'll be right back.
♪ You're one and only T.V. 9 ♪
(upbeat rock blues music)
(rushing water and sea birds)
(uplifting music)
- [Announcer] Day to night
and everything in between.
A vibrant collection of
cultures and activities await
in greater Fort Lauderdale.
Start planning at sunny.org/letsgo.
- [Announcer] The Hyundai
Presidents' Day Sales Event
is going on now!
Get huge savings on our full line
of both cars and SUVs.
Hyundai is also making
some history of its own.
The Hyundai Kona has been named
the 2019 North American
Utility Vehicle of the Year.
Incredible vehicles, monumental savings.
Find yours during the Hyundai
Presidents' Day Sales Event
going on now.
Get a Santa Fe with 0%
APR, plus $500 bonus cash
or $3,000 cash back.
Now extended, an extra $500
for government employees
effected by the shutdown.
- She me The Crown.
Show me Homecoming.
Baby sloth videos on YouTube.
- Do you mind giving someone else a turn?
- Oh, I made myself a
little comfortable here.
- I got a pizza for Amy!
- Yes, that's me!
- [Announcer] Xfinity
lets you search Netflix,
Prime Video, and YouTube
with the sound of your voice.
- And I don't have my wallet.
So...
- [Announcer] That simple, easy, awesome.
Switch to Xfinity and get
started with this great offer.
Plus ask about 4K Ultra HD
in packages that include Netflix.
Call or visit a store today.
- [Announcer] The Presidents
Day sale at MattressFIRM
has been extended!
Today is your last chance
to take home a king
for the price of a queen,
and a queen for the price of a twin.
Save up to $600 store-wide.
Plus you'll also get
a free adjustable base
with your qualifying mattress,
up to a $699 value, free.
Customers like Joe in
California have spoken,
and they're just crazy about this deal.
Hurry in, the deals of the year end today.
Your budget stretches further
at MattressFIRM.
- My gums are irritated.
I don't have to worry about that, do I?
- Actually, you do.
Harmful bacteria lurk
just below the gumline.
- [Announcer] New Crest Gum Detoxify
works below the gumline
to neutralize harmful plaque bacteria
and help reverse early gum damage.
Gum Detoxify from Crest.
- [Announcer] Breathe freely, fast,
with Vicks Sinex.
(inhales through nose)
- My congestion's gone.
(inhales deeply through nose)
I can breathe again!
(sniffs)
Ah!
I can breathe again!
(quick sniff) Oh.
(baby laughs)
- [Announcer] Vicks Sinex.
Breathe on.
- Whoo!
- I'm looking at that truck!
- Wow!
- That's awesome!
- [Announcer] Everyone is excited
about the all new award
winning Chevy models.
- They're all really cool cars.
- Whoo, I love it!
- I can't stop staring at it.
- [Announcer] See what
the excitement's all about
at your local Chevy dealer
and take advantage of
a great deal like this.
Current qualified, competitive lessees
can lease this Malibu
for around $179 a month,
or current GM owners get
$4,250 total cash allowance
on most Malibu models
when you purchase and
finance with GM Financial.
- [Announcer] And now, WUSA9 Sports
brought to you by Xfinity.
- WUSA9 Sports Director Darren Haynes,
he's at spring training with the Nats,
and three things you
just need to know about.
- I'm Darren Haynes at
Nationals' spring training
and here are three
things you need to know.
Bryce Harper is not in West Palm Beach.
The free agent has yet to
sign with a Major League team.
The Nationals reportedly
already offered him
a 300 million dollar deal over ten years,
the same as the Phillies,
who offered him a ten year contract
for 310 million.
How much do you want him on this team?
- Oh, I want him on this team,
and the guys in the clubhouse
want him on this team.
He's one of the best players
in the game right now.
And people in and around this organization
have had a front row seat to really see
how good of a player he is.
But at the end of the day
we can't be sitting around waiting for him
to walk through those doors.
- Here's the second
thing you need to know.
There's another big free
agent out there, people.
Or should I say, use to be free agent?
Former Oriole, Manny Machado,
signed a ten year, 300
million dollar contract
with the Padres.
So what does this all mean?
This could accelerate
things for Bryce Harper
to sign with a team.
I spoke to Nationals
manager, Davey Martinez,
and he says Bryce Harper needs to focus
on what's best for his family.
But at the same time
he's gonna focus on the
players that are here
at spring training.
Speaking of Davey Martinez,
here's something you didn't know about him
for number three.
Hidden talent.
- I can play the bongos.
- Now, these are not bongos, but...
(taps out a rhythm)
- You tap a little bit?
- [Darren] Can you?
- Can you tap?
(taps out a rhythm)
- Who taught you that?
- My dad.
- Great.
- Yeah.
- Good stuff, good stuff.
See, we learned something new today.
Now coming up at 11:00 tonight,
why was today almost like a family reunion
for manager Davey Martinez?
Reporting from West Palm
Beach, I'm Darren Haynes,
WUSA9 Sports.
- [Bruce] Darren's gonna be
with Nats spring training
in Florida all week long.
He's gonna bring you live exclusive access
to the players in our WUSA9 Facebook page.
- Oh, Darren, he's
missing all this tomorrow.
For shame.
- Picked a good week.
And speaking of Facebook Live,
Howard's on there now
if you wanna ask him
questions about the snow
and the sleet and the freezing rain.
- Okay.
- So we'll show you the
snow fall map again.
We have tailored it down a bit.
Three to five north and
west with a plus sign.
One to three in the metro.
A trace to an inch down
into the northern neck
and also southern Maryland.
But I do want to emphasize,
if you're driving up
from southern Maryland,
from Saint Mary's County
through Charles County
tomorrow around 9:00, 10:00,
it's gonna be bad.
It's gonna start to snow quickly,
it will accumulate quickly,
and it will become heavy
also rather quickly.
But, once we get through that we're okay.
We're 56 on Thursday, 50s on Friday,
and let's just jump ahead to 66 on Sunday.
- If some of you can stay
off the road for one day,
I would do it.
That's News at 6:00.
Back at 7:00 with Off Script.
- CBS Evening News is next.
We'll see you all back here at 11:00.
(upbeat poppy music)
- [Announcer] You've
been watching WUSA9 News,
with a weather forecast
rated most accurate
for the last seven years.
(inspiring music)
(two rapid beeps)
(crackling fire)
- [Announcer] Stay warm and cozy
with Gasfireplaces.com.
(crackling fire)
Cyprus Air's Presidents Day sale is here.
Convert your wood burning fireplace to gas
and get up to 80% off with installation
as early as next week.
Visit your nearest showroom.
Or schedule a free in-home visit online
at Gasfireplaces.com.
- [Announcer] Fourth of
July has its fireworks.
Christmas, gifts.
But what about Presidents' Day?
Let's just say the voters
will be very happy.
Announcing our best offers
on America's best selling brand.
You gotta love democracy.
Through February 28th only
get $4,000 total cash on select Ford SUVs.
Hurry to your local Ford dealers
for best selection during the
Presidents' Day Sales Event.
- I never thought I'd say this
but I found bladder leak underwear
that's actually pretty.
Always discreet Boutique.
Hidden inside is a super absorbent core
that quickly turns liquid to gel.
So I feel protected.
And pretty.
Always discreet Boutique.
- Do I use a toothpaste
that whitens my teeth,
or one that's good for my teeth?
Now I don't have to choose.
Crest 3D White.
The whitening therapy collection.
Now with charcoal or coconut oil.
It gently whitens,
plus it has a fortifying
formula to protect your enamel.
Crest.
Healthy, beautiful smiles for life.
- [Announcer] Stronger
is blasting her tumors
without risking her bones.
It's training her good cells
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain,
new hope,
more fight.
It's doing everything in your power
and everything it ours.
Stronger is changing
even faster than they do.
Because we don't just
want your kids to grow up,
we want them to grow up stronger.
(upbeat music)