- This week on America's birthday,
known as Independence
Day or simply July 4th,
Donald Trump threw himself a party.
Ever since he saw that the
French president has a parade,
it's called Bastille Day
and the dictator of
North Korea has a parade,
it's called Authoritarianism,
and that they get to have tanks
and people marching in front
of them and saluting them
and all that stuff, he's
wanted to have one too.
He tried to co-opt other
holidays to get his parade
like Veterans Day or Memorial Day
but the adults in the military
kept pushing him back.
Well no more.
Donald Trump finally got his
special Donald Trump parade.
Rolling tanks down the
streets of your capital,
flying Air Force planes over his head
while he gave an odd
speech about the airports,
the Continental Congress took control of
during the Revolutionary War.
- In June of 1775, the
Continental Congress
created a unified army out
of the revolutionary forces
encamped around Boston and New York
and named after the
great George Washington,
Commander-in-Chief.
The Continental Army
suffered a bitter winter
at Valley Forge, found glory
across the waters of the Delaware
and seized victory from
Cornwallis of Yorktown.
Our army manned the airports,
it rend the ramparts, it
took over the airports,
it did everything it had to do
and it fought McHenry under
the rocket's red glare,
it had nothing but victory.
- Okay!
I'm sure that you know this already
because you paid attention in school,
but just so that it's
said, the Continental Army
was not named after George Washington.
There was no air travel
during the Revolutionary War.
Airplanes weren't even
invented until 1903.
And the Battle at Fort McHenry
happened during The War of 1812!
Details!
In the end, for millions
of your tax dollars,
this what you, well actually
what Donald Trump got.
- On this day, 243 years ago,
our founding fathers pledged their lives,
their fortunes and their sacred honor
to declare Independence and
defend our God-given rights.
- Throwing not an American president
but what looks like an
authoritarian leader.
Festooned by his military and
making a show of force to,
well it's not really clear who.
Because Donald Trump actually
really likes dictators.
Joining me now is Maria Teresa Kumar,
president and CEO of Voto Latino.
Jelani Cobb, professor at
Columbia Journalism School,
Craig Unger, Vanity Fair contributor
and author of "House of
Trump, House of Putin"
and Representative Ted Lieu,
Democrat from California
and a member of the Foreign Affairs
and Judiciary committees.
I wanna go to you first Congressman.
What did you make of it?
Watching an American president
do this thing that Tom Nichols
who's an expert on the
history of the Soviet Union
and of that region, described as looking
like an old Soviet kind of parade.
- Thank you Joy for your question.
Let me just first say
that natural disasters
like earthquakes can strike at any time
and I urge everyone to be prepared
with supplies and a safety plan.
Now to answer your question,
one of the big problems
with Trump's July 4th event,
is that it was a campaign event
paid for by the American taxpayer.
Not only did he divert millions
of dollars to this event,
he also had the Republican
National Committee
give out passes, VIP
passes to major donors.
That was outrageous.
That was really a violation of our ethics
and he made a mockery
of our Independence Day.
- And thank you for mentioning
what's going on in your state.
We just saw two natural disasters
in the state of California.
So this is a time when
the federal government
actually has priorities
that are important,
that we should be spending money on.
Things like making sure,
that states are ready
for natural disasters like
you just saw in your state.
So when you see the President
of the United States
diverting money so that he can have planes
fly over him rather
than spending the money
on important things like that
or maybe uncaging children,
which he's also doing in
the state of California
and Arizona and other places.
As a member of Congress,
is there something
that you guys plan to do about that?
Because this does seem like
a tremendous waste of money.
- Members of Congress can't
even use official resources
to participate in a parade.
In this case, Trump diverted $2.5 million
of National Park fees
to pay for his party.
And I've asked the Federal
Election Commission
to look into this because how can you have
all this taxpayer money do this event
and then have the Republican
National Committee
be involved in such a major way
handing out VIP passes
to their major donors.
- Yeah, and besides that, I
wanna go to you Craig Unger.
You've written a lot about Donald Trump
his Mafia sort of
relationships that he's had
throughout his career, particularly
when it comes to Russia.
This is what Michael McFaul,
who is the former US
Ambassador to Russia tweeted
after Donald Trump's weird parade.
He said, "I knew this was coming."
Tweet from Julia Davis News,
Russia's state TV is obsessively
bashing Trump's low energy,
weak parade with rusty tanks.
The host's LOL at Trump's claim
about Revolutionary War airports,
and other historical flubs.
There's your city upon a hill.
There's your world leader,
and Martians have been defeated.
The fact is that Donald
Trump not only wasted
America's money, to make
himself a campaign commercial,
but he also has subjected
the United States to mockery
because real dictatorships
know what a dictator parade
is supposed to look like Craig.
- Right, well at least sometimes
they get their facts straight.
It's interesting that
if the Russian State TV
is going after Trump, that doesn't happen
without Vladimir Putin's say-so.
It's also interesting
that clip you showed,
the number of historical errors
and it is just extraordinary
and the White House has an
office of speech writing
with lots of researchers and interns
and they fact-check things.
And there are only three possibilities
for that level of transcendental
stupidity to take place.
One is, that that office is completely
filled with people with
room temperature IQ.
The other is that all the
procedures have fallen apart
and they don't exist anymore.
And the third possibility is it sprung
from the brain of Donald Trump
and that is deeply, deeply disturbing.
- There's a lot about it
that's disturbing Jelani.
I wanna go to you on this,
I'm glad that you're here
just to have an historical
context to all of this.
Donald Trump really admires
dictatorships around the world.
He seems to really admire Kim Jong Un.
All of the media has been saying
that this is supposed to
be sort of his version
of the Bastille Day ceremony.
But I pointed out earlier
this week on MSNBC
the whole Bastille Day thing
is about sending a message to dictators.
That's what the whole
Bastille Day parade is about.
This is clearly not that,
because Donald Trump likes dictators.
That's not what you're trying
to send a message doing.
So in your mind, what is this,
what was the message of what you saw,
I don't know if you watched it
but what was the message
that you think came out
of what Donald Trump did this week?
- Oh it was pure and
grandiosity and self-inflation.
And so one of the things I
think that's significant here
is that the United
States at least in theory
is supposed to operate on the doctrine
that we are a nation of laws,
that no one is above the law
and that the constitution is
the fundamental authority.
That is a different position,
fundamentally different position
than a state in which the personality
or the authoritarian leader
is the head of all interests and ideas
within the state.
And so what Donald Trump did,
was essentially hijack this idea
and turn it into something
that was supposed to glorify himself.
This kinda interesting paradox here
which is that several years ago,
I did a Fulbright Fellowship
and I spent an entire semester in Moscow
teaching at Moscow State University
and at the end of the semester,
there was the May 9th Celebration.
Anybody who has been to Russia
or knows about their
history post World War II,
May 9th is a gigantic celebration
that happens each year,
somewhere between the 4th of July
and New Year's and it is a recognition
of the Soviet defeat of the Nazi threat,
an existential threat that confronted them
during World War II.
So it's a huge and I'm able
to be there for the parade
and there's just this kind
of complete procession
of military vehicles.
There are missiles, there are tanks,
there are armored
vehicles, there are Jeeps
and it looks like an army
amassing for an invasion.
And so someone turns to me and says,
do you do the same thing
in the United States
on the 4th of July.
I said no, this would never
happen in the United States
because they in the United States believe,
we believe that there should
be a really clear distinction
between civilian authority
and military might
and that our authority is
supposed to, at least in theory
stem from our laws and our moral beliefs.
And what Donald Trump did,
was essentially invert that
to create it as a kind of satirical almost
emulation of something that
he sees in Vladimir Putin.
We should recognize this as
the anti-democratic movement
that it actually was.
- Yeah, Maria Teresa, there's an example.
I mean Eugene Robinson
made a similar point
when he talked about the fact
that Trump tried to make himself look big
by doing this piece.
A little bit of what
Eugene, what he wrote,
it was clear from the beginning
that Independence Day
meant nothing more to Trump
than an opportunity to choreograph
a made for television re-election event
and give himself an obscenely
expensive ego message.
It invoked mockery.
There's a cartoon, we're gonna show here
that's drawn on what
airplanes would look like
during the Revolutionary War.
It's a picture of Ben Franklin
attached to two kites, there it is
and this is by somebody I know.
This is by the great Natalie
Johnson who drew that.
Here's the reality, Donald Trump it seems
wants to be seen as this big man.
He wants to be seen as this grand leader
of this great military
but what he actually can accomplish
through his own, the quality of the staff
that he has around him,
is he can't do that.
He can't do what Jelani
just talked about, right?
The reality was right,
even in the case of Russia
which now is an adversary
of the United States,
during World War II they
were fighting the Nazis.
So if they're doing a big celebration
and talking about
defeating the Nazi Empire,
they're sort of sending a
message again to dictators.
There are only two kinds of these parades.
There's that, and there's
the one like in North Korea.
Trump is tying to do it
because I think he thinks
he's emulating it, he
doesn't even know how.
- Or really why!
- This is to Maria.
- We're the largest military
operators in the world.
We don't have to show that
type of display of force
because the world already knows it.
And what I found so disappointing
when it came to the July 4th is July 4th
is to commemorate our roots as Americans.
Where we come from,
the fact that we may have
fled different countries
or we came here because we recognize that.
Our Americanism, our DNA is this idea
that we're a nation of immigrants
and we have strength and
we don't have to show
military might because the
world already knows it.
And what Donald Trump did
was such a sad display
because he didn't have the courage
to actually join the military
when his card was up.
He instead deferred on bone spurs.
And so he basically, not
only deteriorates the flag
but also the meaning of what
it means to be an American
and what it means to be July 4th,
what it means to come
together as a nation.
The reason that presidents
don't show up on July 4th
and don't make it about them,
is because it's one country
under one flag and one unity.
It's not supposed to be partisan
and what instead he did is
he created a campaign rally,
trying to differentiate and divide us
and what I espouse and what
I think was really beautiful
is that you still saw
families on that lawn saying,
"I'm apolitical, I'm here to
share it with my families."
And that's what we should remind people
of what July 4th is.
We don't have to show military might,
we don't have to scare the world,
we know what we are, we know who we are
and we know that we do it with justice.
The fact that he can do this
in the backdrop of caging children,
that is not who we are
and the more that we
can actually make sure
that we are standing
strong to those values,
despite about what I call this
aberration in our history,
we have to make sure that
we are very clear minded
of what it means to be American
and what it means to be democratic
and what it means to be fair and just.
- Yeah, very quickly just
let everybody go through
one last chance.
Jelani, do you think that what you saw,
what Donald Trump made us look stronger
or weaker as a country?
- Oh absolutely weaker.
The worst part of it is that,
had this actually not
been an inept display
of pseudo-authoritarianism,
we still would have looked weaker.
If he had done this correctly,
in air quotes, correctly,
we would have looked weaker.
But now we look doubly weak,
because it is a poor imitation
of something that was
never meant to be imitated
in the first place.
- Yeah, very quickly
and to go to you Craig.
When the Russians look at us,
they're already laughing at us.
Donald Trump thinks
they're his best friends.
Are they his friends
or is he now a subject
of even mockery to them?
- Well, I think he is subject to mockery
and I think Jelani is absolutely right.
The images that come away from it today,
are that we have concentration
camps on the border,
we have tanks by the Lincoln Memorial.
The mall is, there was
an interesting piece
in the Washington Post.
The architecture is about reconciliation.
It's by the Lincoln
Memorial, our original sin
was slavery, we had a Civil War
and this is where we were
supposed to have reconciliation
and instead, today we have images of tanks
and the whole crisis at the border.
- I'm gonna give you the
last word Congressman
because you are a member
of the Air Force I believe.
You've served in the military.
As a person who actually did
serve, unlike Donald Trump,
when you saw tanks rolling
down the nation's capital,
your thoughts were what?
- Having served in active
duty in the military,
we've been trained to not participate
in partisan campaign events.
There was a Department
of Defense directive
that prohibits military members
from showing up in uniform
at a campaign rally.
This was a massive
taxpayer-funded campaign rally
with the Republican National Committee
handing out VIP passes.
It really eroded what should be
a non-partisan military and
that was sad and disappointing.
- Thank you all for being here
and sending out really good thoughts
to your state Congressman Lieu.
Thank you very much all of you.
Maria Teresa is gonna be back.
Jelani Cobb, Craig Unger
and Congressman Ted Lieu,
thank you guys very much and coming up,
as Donald Trump celebrated
himself on the 4th of July,
people looking for a better future
were locked in cages
on our southern border.
Great, more on that next.
(dramatic music)
- [Announcer] Everyone loves the benefits
of compression socks
but they're just so hard
to get on, until now!
Introducing the all new
Copper Fit Energy Socks.
Redesigned for the first
ever easy on, easy off fit,
to help reduce swelling,
relieve tired aching muscles
and provide energizing support.
A new blend of stretch fabric
for the most comfortable, easy
on easy off compression fit.
- Being a SWAT Commander,
we're trained to win.
The Copper Fit Energy Socks,
they didn't feel like
other compression sock.
It totally exceeded my expectations.
- [Announcer] Our most
powerful copper-infused fabric
woven into our easy on,
easy off compression sock
to help reduce swelling discomfort
from prolonged sitting or standing.
- I'm 38 and 1/2 weeks pregnant.
Copper Fit Energy Socks works beautifully.
- [Announcer] Extra support
around the arch and ankles.
For increased support and relief
of muscle aches and pains.
- I'm so excited about this sock.
I'm so much more energized to go do things
after a day of work.
They just slip right
on, yet they still have
that same compression that you want.
- [Announcer] A soft cushion foot bed
for all day comfort.
- I'm on my feet at least
nine or 10 hours a day.
These were fantastic.
A lot of compression socks
are a little too thin
especially for what I do.
With Copper Fit, I can
wear these every day.
- [Announcer] Feel more
energized, feel more active,
just feel better.
- They just hug your leg.
It relieves all the
pressure that you have.
I have so much energy, I can go.
Hey, you wanna dance.
- [Announcer] The first
ever easy on easy off
compression sock, the most
comfortable compression sock
you will ever wear.
Get your Copper Fit
Energy socks now online
at getenergysocks.com for only $19.99.
Call 1-800-290-8143.
Order right now and we'll include
a second pair of compression socks free.
- I've never felt anything like it before.
- No more pain, no more swelling,
no more achy tired feet.
- I can never go back to
regular compression socks again.
- [Announcer] Don't settle for ordinary.
Ask for the original by name.
(crowd cheering)
- Coach, it's kinda hard to see the ball.
- I've been there.
I had a TV service with
hardly any sports in 4K.
Couldn't see any of the quality details.
I switched to DIRECTV.
Now I get the most live sports in 4K.
- So, how does that help me?
- It really doesn't, I don't
know why I told you that.
Go get 'em sport.
- [Announcer] Live
sports that aren't in 4K,
are just kinda TV.
Don't just kinda TV, DIRECTV.
Don't have 4K, call 1-855-WATCH-4K
and ask for it today.
- [Announcer] This
summer, all eyes will be
on the US Women's National Team
in the FIFA Women's World Cup.
(upbeat music)
Over 153 hours of coverage.
Live from France, the 2019
FIFA Women's World Cup
on Fox, FS1 and FS2.
Don't miss all 52 matches of
the FIFA Women's World Cup
live in stunning 4K on DIRECTV.
If you don't have 4K, ask for it today.
- [Announcer] Download
the TouchNote app now.
- How do you know how to run,
when you've never done anything
remotely like this before?
- We're prepared to do it in a novel way,
in an original way and we wanna make sure
that we're writing our own playbook.
- Do you think that we should
keep troops in Afghanistan?
- I do not and I believe
that we need to do it though
in a responsible way.
- Where do you see your party right now?
- It's going to be how do we
think government should work
and who do we think
government should work for?
(dramatic music)
- What we saw today was unconscionable.
No child should ever be
separated from their parent.
- The mothers, the abuelas, the tias,
the madres that I sat with,
who wept openly in our arms.
- Never forget the
image of being in a cell
and seeing 15 women, tears
coming down their faces
as they talked about being
separated from their children
about having no running water.
- In fact one of the women said,
that she was told by
an agent to drink water
out of the toilet.
- This week Democratic lawmakers
once again saw for themselves
the shameful conditions
that migrant children and adults
have been forced to live in.
Specifically at a detention
facility in Clint, Texas.
Conditions that the Department
of Homeland Security's
Inspector General confirmed
in a report this week.
Now let me read to you
some of the findings.
Quote, children at three
of the five border patrol facilities
that we visited had no access to showers.
At these facilities
children had limited access
to a change of clothes.
Border patrol had few spare clothes
and no laundry facilities.
While all facilities had infant formula,
diapers, baby wipes and juice
and snacks for children,
we observed that two facilities
had not provided children
access to hot meals.
But Customs and Border Patrol,
were so desperate to dispel
these firsthand accounts
from lawmakers and from activists
that one of its chiefs filmed a video
showing a supply room filled
with an abundance of clothing
and hygienic supplies, as
well as clean drinking areas
at a detention facility, wait for it,
three hundred miles away in Arizona.
There it is.
Back with me, Maria Teresa Kumar
and also joining me, Andrea Pitzer
who's a journalist and
author of "One Long Night:
"A Global History of Concentration Camps"
and Elora Mukherjee who's a director
of the Immigrants Rights
Clinic at Columbia Law School
and Elora is also a lawyer who has visited
detention centers at the southern border
for the last 12 years.
And Elora, thank you for being here.
I'm gonna start with you.
I wanna play for you a
little bit of a video
that was obtained of a 12-year old girl,
a 12 year-old migrant.
This was her account for
being detained for two weeks.
It's in Spanish, for those
of you who are watching,
so you'll have to just read the subtitles
if you don't speak
Spanish but hear you go.
(speaks foreign language)
Elora, we've heard stories of little kids
being forced to take care
of other little kids.
Children sleeping on the ground
in nothing but a diaper,
children saying that they
only got one meal a day.
We heard this little
girl's horrifying story
of being detained, is this legal?
- No, this is absolutely not legal.
Federal law provides for protections
for children in Federal
Immigration custody.
The 1997 Flores Settlement Agreement
requires that the Federal government
provide safe and sanitary conditions
for children in its custody.
A law from 2008 which was passed
with unanimous bipartisan support
and passed by President George W. Bush
says that children must not be detained
by Customs and Border Patrol
for any longer than 72 hours.
The conditions that we're learning about,
what we hear, what I smelled
when I was at these facilities,
it is unlawful and illegal.
- And then Elora, how can they,
this is what I have not understood
and I'm gonna go to you first
and then I'm gonna go
to Maria Teresa Kumar
because we've talked for a long time
about why they might be doing it.
They're holding kids for
50 days, 40 days, 30 days.
They're holding them as if almost like,
it's like they're
ransom, they can't leave.
How can they get away
with it, if it is illegal?
- It is illegal and
what's important to know
is that most of these children
have family members in the United States
who are desperate to
have their children back.
More than 80% of children released
from the federal government
are housed and cared for
and loved for by their own family members.
We need immediate congressional oversight
and pressure on this administration
to release children from detention
as quickly as possible.
And while children are detained,
they must be treated humanely.
- Yeah, and you know Maria Teresa Kumar,
I have to go to you on this because,
we have been down there,
you have been there
much more than I have,
obviously Elora has been there.
I'm not a lawyer, it strikes
me as completely illegal
to hold children in this manner
when as Elora just said
they have family to go to.
Donald Trump calls that catch-and-release
and says he's not doing it.
Why in your view are they
holding these children?
Is it the money that they're making?
I mean it's 750 bucks a day
to hold kids in these camps.
Is it straight money?
Why are they not letting them go?
- I think there's a couple of things.
I think one is political fodder.
It shows that he is the
strong-fisted person
that is basically making sure that,
they're trying to use this as a deterrent.
He didn't come up with this.
This is Steve Miller, his senior advisor
with his fingerprints all over it.
But it allows, it's good for
political fodder for his base,
that he is being tough
and that it's really
the parents' fault that they came here.
But two, there's a lot
of money to be made.
The moment that Donald Trump
was elected into office,
all of a sudden the private
detention facilities,
the for-profit detention facilities,
their stock prices went,
literally went on the rise.
The former Chief of Staff John Kelly
who advised President Trump
and before was head of the DHS,
he was also one of the architects of this.
Guess where John Kelly is now.
He is now on the board of advisors
to one of the largest detention
for-profit facilities.
He has actually gone down
to Homestead down in Florida
which is one of the largest facilities
that houses close to 3200 minors.
And they keep them for a long time.
Unlike President Obama who did have
the moniker of deporter in chief,
President Obama processed
individuals and deported them.
This president has little
intention of deporting them.
These children who are minors
are not supposed to be in
custody for more than 20 days.
In some cases, they languish
in there for months.
In some cases, almost a year.
And it's clear that the
only way that you do it
is that you ensure that someone
is making a lot of profit
and you do it away from the cameras,
you do it away from the American public
and you do it almost in secret.
The fact that this is basically,
you have some ICE agents
actually coming out
and anonymously showing pictures
of what is happening in the facilities.
They're trying to also ring the red light
of this is not normal, this is illegal
and we need the American
people to stand up for it.
The fact that the United Nations
have declared that the United States
is in violation of children's human rights
should be screaming at
the top of the lungs
of every single American
saying this is not who we are.
And we have to make this
a political campaign issue
because this is what
we actually stand for.
- Andrea, we've had a
whole bunch of people
getting upset and debating
over what you call these camps.
I don't know what else you would call it
other than concentration camps.
If these children are
being deliberately held
longer than they're
legally allowed to be held,
they won't let them go.
They seem to be displaying their misery
really to sort of entertain,
I don't know what it is
that they're trying to
show the American people
but they seem to want us to know
that they're doing this to these kids.
We even had a young man,
who was allegedly shamed.
They hung a sign on him,
saying I like men, in Spanish
and put a sign on him
to try to humiliate him.
This reminds me almost of
the way that we behaved
at Abu Ghraib, where we
were just trying to display
the mockery of these people.
I don't understand what's going on here.
I don't understand how it
can possibly be going on
and that no one's stopping it,
your thoughts Andrea.
- So, look it's no surprise
that there are echos
of prior camp systems from Abu Ghraib
and going back more than 100 years even,
in what we're seeing on the border today.
The turn of the 20th century,
Emily Hobhouse went
down to southern Africa
and was shocked that the British
weren't providing soap to
children and women in detention
so that they could prevent
contagious diseases.
Tens of thousands of people
would die in those camps
while parliament argued
over whether it was fair
to call them concentration camps.
In Germany, in 1933 a
man named Hans Beimler
was arrested and taken to Dachau
where the Nazis put a sign
around his neck to humiliate him.
So we've seen this all before.
We've seen the humiliating signs, no soap,
arguments over what to call it,
overcrowding, deaths
from contagious diseases.
What we have is not a death
camp system like Auschwitz
but it is a concentration camp system.
It's a malevolent system
that has deep roots in a polarized society
that is willing to do
harm to vulnerable people.
And the thing is that, if the
authorities don't intervene,
we know what's going to happen.
We're gonna move to the next stage
of concentration camp abuses,
which are gonna show up not as
negligence but as atrocities.
- I'm gonna ask all of
you to please come back--
- Can I just add something--
- Very quickly.
- Okay!
- Yeah, very quickly.
- So Joy I think the bigger issue too
is that we know that a lot of these folks
that are getting these
government contracts
actually served as security guards
for Afghanistan and for Iraq.
They have no business being
surrounded by children.
- Yeah, absolutely. I wanna
have you guys come back.
Because we wanna try to think about
what these children can do.
I don't know if there's some lawsuit.
We need to figure out what to do next.
Thank you very much Maria Teresa Kumar,
I'm sorry I'm out of time.
Andrea Pitzer, Elora Mukherjee,
thank you all three very
much and later on this hour
we are gonna talk about this
disturbing new information
that we're learning about the culture
at the Border Protection Agency.
So please stay tuned for that.
And coming up next, even
after he was slapped down
by the Supreme Court, Donald
Trump is still not giving up
on his attempts to rig the census.
It's just getting better
and better and better.
We'll be right back.
(dramatic music)
- How many people love
you unconditionally?
While you ponder that,
consider adopting a rescue pet.
There are six and 1/2 million of them,
they all need a forever home.
It would mean the world to them
and they will love you
forever, The More You Know.
- [Announcer] One word describes
the perfect family vacation
on the world's best beach.
♪ Makes me go wow ♪
♪ Makes me go wow wow ♪
♪ Wa wa wa wa wow ♪
♪ Wa wa wa wow ♪
♪ Help me sing it ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Just wow ♪
- [Announcer] Experience the wow factor
at Beaches Resorts, where
everything's included
for everyone.
Call 1-800-Beaches.
- [Announcer] Stay tuned to get a free pan
from Granite Stone.
Stuck on eggs, burnt on butter,
you can scrub and scrape
but you can't escape
the nightmare of your sticky pans.
Introducing the Granite Stone pan,
the all new durable non-stick pan.
No butter or oil needed.
Watch, we melted down this
sticky candies in Granite Stone
and it just doesn't stick.
We cooked a half a dozen
eggs, bacon, cheese
and tomato breakfast with no butter or oil
and it just doesn't stick.
Look, caramels, chocolate and cheese,
unreal for any other pan
but not for Granite Stone.
It just doesn't stick.
Granite Stone will be the
last pan you'll ever need
because it's pressed from
a solid aluminum disk
for even heat conduction.
Then coated three times with our durable
Granite Stone finish.
Granite Stone is metal
utensil safe and won't scratch
and talk about non-stick, this salmon
cooks skin side down with
no added butter or oil,
just doesn't stick.
This steak is perfectly
seared just like the pros.
And because Granite Stone is
oven rated to 500 degrees,
we bake this upside down
pan pizza to perfection
and it just doesn't stick.
Fire flambe, delicious cherries jubilee.
Plus it's PFOA free and
100% dishwasher safe.
Call or go online to get
your Granite Stone pan
for the special TV discount
price of just $19.99.
Granite Stone is so durable,
it comes with a 10-year warranty.
And with every order, you're going to get
a Granite Stone single serve
egg pan absolutely free.
It's the perfect size
for personalized eggs,
omelets or frittatas that slide right out.
It makes the best bacon egg
and cheese sandwich quick.
Yours absolutely free.
We'll even ship your entire order free.
That's right, free shipping.
You get it all at incredible value.
Here's how to order.
- [Announcer] To order
call 1-800-615-7903.
That's 1-800-615-7903 or order online
at buygranitestone.com.
That's 1-800-615--
- I just couldn't stay
in shape like I used to.
But luckily I found Nugenix.
- [Announcer] Nugenix has a
unique man-boosting formula
that helps increase your
free testosterone level.
To get a complementary bottle text--
- BEST!
- To 42424.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Want a $10 Amazon gift card.
Sign up for CuriosityStream today
and get a $10 Amazon gift card on us.
You'll get access to thousands
of non-fiction titles.
- [Announcer] That's affirmative.
- [Announcer] We've got
something for everyone.
- You don't have to look
any further than this.
- [Announcer] $19.99 gets you
one year of CuriosityStream.
- That really ignites the imagination.
- [Announcer] And a $10 Amazon gift card.
Sign up now.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Get a
free "Mesothelioma" book
from mesobook.com.
- [Announcer] People
who have been diagnosed
with mesothelioma have many questions.
That's why we offer this free book.
- [Announcer] Call toll
free at 1-800-821-8383.
- [Announcer] Visit casper.com today.
(dramatic music)
- Okay!
Officials in Southern California
are assessing the damage
after the second powerful
earthquake in the region
in just the last two days.
Friday's quake had a magnitude of 7.1
and was centered in the
desert city of Ridgecrest.
It was felt more than 100
miles away in Los Angeles
and in Las Vegas.
It rattled homes and businesses
and sparked fires and power outages.
At a baseball game between
the Los Angeles Dodgers
and the San Diego Padres,
Dodgers Stadium seemed to shake and roll
for nearly a minute, but
the players played on.
Friday's quake comes one day
after a 6.4 magnitude
earthquake in the same region.
And officials say there
will likely be more.
Stay with MSNBC throughout the day
for the latest on this story.
And up next in AM Joy, Trump
and his far-right allies
want to rig the census to
beat back a changing America.
But since he's Donald Trump,
he may have already tanked his own case.
- [Announcer] When cravings
come on strong, be stronger.
With new Nicorette coded ice
mint, layered with flavor,
it's the first and only
coded Nicotine lozenge
for an amazing taste that
outlasts your craving.
New Nicorette ice mint.
- [Announcer] Paul, you're
the greatest neighbor.
You help us find the best
home improvement pros.
Get quotes and research
prices for our home projects.
- That, that's not me.
That's HomeAdvisor.
You can't expect your
neighbors to do it all
so just ask HomeAdvisor.
- Introducing Nutrisystem's July 4th sale.
Save 50%, yes 50%.
- [Announcer] Lose up to
13 pounds and seven inches
in your first month.
Order your 28-day plan and get one week
of high protein shakes, with probiotics
to help shrink your belly free.
- And there's even a money back guarantee.
- [Announcer] Save 50% off every program.
- Grab this special offer right now
and start losing today.
- [Announcer] Go online
or call 877-651-FIT6
right now to save 50%.
- Hi, I'm Alex Schulze.
- And I'm Andrew Cooper.
- In 2015, we took a surf
trip to Bali, Indonesia
and saw firsthand just how bad
the world's plastic
pollution crisis really is.
We wanted to make it our mission
to solve this problem, and we have.
- [Andrew] We started cleaning
the ocean by ourselves.
Until 2017, when we started
our ocean cleanup company 4ocean.
- Now, we've become the world's largest
ocean cleanup company,
employing captains and crews,
seven days a week to clean
our oceans and coastlines.
We've operated out of
27 different countries,
and to date, we've removed over
two million pounds of trash
from the ocean.
And now, we're inviting you
to join the clean ocean movement.
- [Andrew] All of our cleanup
efforts are funded entirely
through the sale of our bracelet.
The 4ocean bracelet is
made from our ocean plastic
and the recycled glass
bottles that we collect.
- Every bracelet purchase
helps fund the removal
of one pound of trash from the ocean
and supports the 4ocean cleanup movement.
- So visit 4ocean.com today
to become part of the solution.
(soft music)
- [Announcer] CoQ10 is the number one
cardiologist recommended supplement
for people taking
cholesterol-lowering statin drugs.
Qunol with three times better absorption
than regular CoQ10, has the number one
cardiologist recommended form of CoQ10.
Qunol, the better CoQ10.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Introducing
the Blackstone griddle.
Outdoor cooking without the compromise.
Log on now to blackstoneproducts.com.
- Four dozen roses can be
beautiful, but painful.
And I want the guests to
smell flowers, not pain cream.
- [Announcer] New Aspercreme
dry spray with lidocaine.
Sprays on instantly dry.
- [Woman] No greasy mess, no odor.
All they smell are roses.
- [Announcer] New Aspercreme dry spray.
- [Man] The only person
who's ever stopped doomsday
doesn't exist any more.
- I have to at least try.
It's time for this madness to end.
Enough Kryptonian blood has been spilled.
- Is that it?
- Not even close.
- [Man] You thought you were
him, you are no Superman.
(dramatic music)
- The census, is a
constitutionally mandated operation
that we are required to
implement every 10 years.
It is one of the most vital
and sensitive things that
we do in our government.
I want to know why this
question was magically added
after we have seen that
a political operative
knew and detailed an intent to intimidate
racial and immigrant communities
for a partisan purpose.
- A recent Supreme Court
decision last month
in which Chief Justice John Roberts
sided with the liberals on the court,
made it clear, the majority on the court
saw right through the Trump
administration's attempts
to rig the constitutionally
required United States census
to try and take money and resources away
from non-white people and immigrants.
The Trump administration's
attempts to pretend
that they really wanted to
add a citizenship question
to the census to help them
enforce the Voting Rights Act,
were easily seen right through.
And while the career lawyers
at the Justice Department
seemed content to listen to the court,
apparently Donald Trump was not.
After going on a Twitter tirade
apparently after canoodling
with his far-right allies
Donald Trump has ordered
the DOJ to try again.
Now, a federal judge in Maryland
has ordered a new version
of the case to be heard.
On Friday Trump invented a new power
that he thinks he has as president.
Saying that he's considering
an executive order
to force the citizenship
question on to the census.
- [Reporter] Are you going to issue
an executive order on the census?
- We're thinking about doing
that. It's one of the ways,
we have four or five ways we can do it.
It's one of the ways
that we're thinking about
doing it very seriously.
We're doing well on the census.
We can also add an addition on,
so we can sort the printing now
and maybe do an addendum after
we get a positive decision.
So we're working on a lot of things
including an executive order.
- Well it should go without saying
that you cannot overrule
a Supreme Court decision
with an executive order.
Should go without saying
but I guess we still have to say it.
Joining me now is MSNBC
legal analyst Maya Wiley.
@AdamSerwer of The
Atlantic and Latosha Brown,
co-founder of Black Voters Matter.
Maya, can one overrule a
Supreme Court decision,
I'll just have you answer it,
by having an executive order?
- No!
(laughs)
- Excellent!
So let's move on to the next question.
- No I mean but seriously--
- I think it's important
just to make it clear.
- Well I think what's
really important here
is even Justice Roberts in his opinion,
said that judicial review is
not just an empty vehicle.
That it has to have meaning.
He was explicit in the opinion.
Think about this, a Chief
Justice of the Supreme Court
felt the need to say that in an opinion.
That is astounding and
Donald Trump has proven
why it was necessary to say.
Department of Justice lawyers right now
are trying to figure out how to do
what they have an oath to do,
which is uphold the laws
of the United States.
And there is no higher
legal vehicle in the land
in terms of how to
understand our constitution
or interpret our statutes,
than the Supreme Court.
- And you know Adam,
there's the story that's
sort of enveloping here
is that Donald Trump gets slapped down
by the Supreme Court.
He then is canoodling with
his friends on the far-right
and maybe the alt-right,
maybe the people from his
former folks like Steve Bannon,
whoever he was talking to.
Then he gets mad, he
does this tweet storm,
where he says that it's fake,
that they're not gonna
fight to get this question
onto the census. So he
puts up that as true,
which is just a straight out lie.
And now you have the Department of Justice
twisting itself into knots to
try to figure out a way to do
what they've been told to do,
which is to still find a way
to get this issue onto the census.
And we know from the
reporting that's out there
that the original reason for it
was that they wanted to defund
areas that had a lot of immigrants in it,
especially non-white immigrants.
They wanna give white voters an advantage
by only counting citizens knowing that,
something like 6.5 million people
probably wouldn't even answer
the census if it was on there.
The fact that they're
making it this blatant,
your thoughts.
- Well, I just wanna say one thing.
This is not a question of far-right,
this is the Republican establishment
that hatched this scheme for
weakening the voting influence
of voters of color to
increase white voting power.
This is an absolutely
establishment Republican scheme
that Donald Trump recognizes is important
if the Republican Party
wants to keep winning in elections
in a diversifying country.
They need to figure out a way
to make white votes count more.
And when they went to the Supreme Court,
they gave them a fictional reason
and of all the conservative justices
on the Supreme Court, only Roberts
was willing to say it was fictional.
The other Supreme Court justices
said that the plaintiffs were acting
like conspiracy theorists in suggesting
that the Commerce Secretary was lying.
Well now the president has confirmed it.
This is about districting,
this is about diluting
the minority vote.
This is not about enforcing
the Voting Rights Act.
And everyone knew that was a pretext.
But what they tried to do was
not simply lie to the court.
Not simply lie to the American people
but tell them the thing
that they were seeing
in front of their eyes was false.
- Yeah, and just to show you all the,
and thank you for making that point
because this has been a long term thing
trying to game and game
and game the system
because they know
demographics are changing
and they don't want it
to change their power,
lemme just play the Donald Trump soundbite
that goes with what Adam was just saying
which is where Donald Trump admits
that it's about districting.
It's about using the census to increase
the power of his side, take a listen.
- Well you need it for many reasons.
Number one you need it for Congress,
you need it for Congress, for districting.
You need it for appropriations,
where are the funds going,
how many people are there?
Are they citizens, are they not citizens?
You need it for many reasons.
- Maya, normally when
somebody is that blatant
about admitting that their whole reason
that they're saying they're going
in front of the court for is a lie,
that would be the end of it.
But Donald Trump has gotten
away with this before.
He said that the Muslim
ban was a Muslim ban
and then he said, no, no, I didn't mean it
and the court pretended he never said it.
So, do we have a risk here,
that the partisans on the court
and maybe that includes Roberts.
He's not been a huge fan of voting rights.
Could they just change their reason
and then slide this right
past the Supreme Court?
- It's a little bit
complicated but procedurally.
But let's say this, one of the things
that Chief Justice Roberts did,
was spent about 22 pages
saying why the administration
could put this question on the census
despite the fact that the careerists,
the people who behave
in a non-partisan way
in the Census Bureau said no,
we don't think this question should go on
in order to do what we
need to do as a census.
That's really important
and what the minority
on the court said, what the
liberals on the court said
was, we actually don't
think the whole first part
of that opinion is right.
We think that this
arbitrary and capricious
which is the legal language for,
aint no reason for this, no good reason.
That the fact that the
careerists said, no this is bad,
means it shouldn't happen.
And just one more thing I just wanna add.
2010, Republicans underfunded this census
even before Trump was elected.
- Yeah absolutely and they
sort of made war on it.
Let me go to you quickly Natasha,
because well how will
this look on the ground?
If people are afraid to
answer the census, then what?
- I think part of the problem if people
are afraid to answer the census,
what you're gonna see is you're gonna see
a gross under-count.
You're gonna particularly
see an under-count
in communities of color
and the challenge with that
is there over $800 million of aid
that is actually, goes by census data.
So you'll see a gross
under-count because of this.
But I think that there's another issue
that I just wanna raise
around the president.
That we really have a rogue president
that in this process in particular,
here is executive that's saying that
immediately after the
Supreme Court ruling,
he's actually saying that I'm
considering these options.
One, I'm considering this
option around executive order
and then the second thing he's saying
he's considering the option
of having an addendum.
This is a president that
does not even respect
the law of the land.
I really think that we're
in a constitutional crisis
and we don't need to
act like this is normal.
This is not normal,
this is not acceptable.
This is beyond, he took a oath
and swore that he would actually
uphold the law of the land.
Yet we're seeing this
play out very differently.
I think we need to make the distinction
that here it is, that immediately
after the Supreme Court made a decision,
he says that he's going to do
whatever he wants to do anyway
and we've gotta take that seriously.
- Yeah absolutely!
Well hopefully there's a plan.
We're gonna have you guys come back
and talk about this more.
Maya and Adam will be back,
and Latosha Brown we'll have you back
to talk about what the plan is gonna be
if he's somehow able to thwart the law.
All right, and coming up,
the secret Facebook group
of Border Patrol agents
that is raising new questions
about the treatment of migrants
and the culture of the CBP, that's next.
(dramatic music)
- [Announcer] Your brain
changes as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain,
with an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen, healthier brain, better life.
- [Announcer] Fidelity
is redefining value.
Introducing zero account
fees for brokerage accounts.
And zero minimums to open an account.
At Fidelity, those zeros really add up.
- Article just spoke to me.
It was affordable but
it was also the design
and the quality of it.
Very modern, it's very fresh
and makes me feel at home.
Absolutely amazing.
Beautiful modern furniture.
Shop article.com.
- Pain thinks it makes the rules,
but the rules just changed.
New Icy Hot Lidocaine dry spray.
Instant dry technology.
No mess, no residue, fast-acting relief.
Rise from pain.
New Icy Hot Lidocaine dry spray.
- Shh!
I got a secret.
If you're wondering how I stay so active
and energetic these
days, and I know you are,
it's my Safe Step Walk-In Tub.
Oh yeah!
I know what you're thinking,
Terry I'm not ready for a walk-in tub yet.
Well, did you know that Safe
Step now offers a hybrid tub?
Now you can choose to take a relaxing
therapeutic bath or a stand-up shower.
- [Announcer] Terry
Bradshaw's secret is revealed.
Now it's your turn to get the comfort
and convenience of Safe
Step's new hybrid tub
and shower in one.
As part of Terry's special TV offer,
call now and get a free shower package,
that's an $800 value free.
- And get this, it's bath
with a lifetime warranty.
Yoo hoo!
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-277-0792
and get your free shower package.
Terry's special TV offer
is for a limited time.
So please, call now.
- Treat yourself, trust me.
Your body will thank you.
(upbeat music)
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Oh ♪
- [Announcer] Beaches
Resorts, everything's included
for everyone, generation everyone.
Call 1-800-Beaches.
- With all that USAA offers,
why go with anybody else?
We know their rates are good,
we know that they're always
gonna take care of us.
- It was a instant savings
and I should have changed a long time ago.
- We're the Tenny's and
we're USAA members for life.
- [Announcer] Call USAA and start saving
on insurance today.
- [Announcer] Oh my, this
Heinz mayonnaise is so creamy.
One day you'll tell
your grandkids about it.
And they'll say, grandpas just
tell us about Humpty Dumpty
and you'll say he broke
his pelvis or whatever.
Now back to my creamy Heinz mayonnaise.
Heinz mayonnaise, unforgettably creamy.
(upbeat music)
♪ Summer lights ♪
♪ Keeping me up ♪
♪ I wanna waste time ♪
♪ Just looking up at the sky ♪
♪ Follow stars ♪
♪ Run run and fall ♪
♪ Like we're 16 ♪
♪ Dreaming in the dark ♪
♪ Love the wind in my hair ♪
♪ As I drive my car ♪
- [Announcer] Rate now,
lease the INFINITI QX50
for 379 a month, plus get
a $1000 summer bonus now
during the INFINITY + Summer Sales Event.
- This is political insanity.
When you need a passionate
start to the morning.
- Name one of the Democratic contenders,
name one that you are
positive can beat Trump.
You need your Morning Joe.
Weekdays at six, on MSNBC.
(dramatic music)
- 52% of the force is Latino.
And a lot of people ask me,
how do they get Latino people
then to behave this way
against people who are their own heritage
and their own culture?
And it's because in the academy,
they mandate and they teach the agents
to use racist terms for migrants
so that they see these people as other
and that they're not like them.
It does have an effect.
It's condoned, and when it happens
and if somebody complains,
everybody groups together,
specifically more the male side
and they protect each other.
- A second formerly secret Facebook group
frequented by current and former
Customs and Border Patrol
agents has been unearthed.
CNN obtained screenshots from two sources
familiar with the Facebook pages
that contain vulgar and
sexually explicit posts
mocking migrants and demeaning lawmakers
like Congresswoman
Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez.
It comes on the heels of a separate,
secret Facebook group that
was exposed earlier this week.
NBC News has not independently verified
these Facebook groups or posts
and back with me Maya
Wiley and Adam Serwer.
Adam, you have posts
like feeling kinda cute,
might separate some families today, IDK,
for I don't know.
You have another group member
that was apparently on these posts,
who posted a photo of the father
and his 23-month old daughter,
they both died lying
face down the Rio Grande.
Asked if the photo could have been faked
because the bodies were so quote, clean.
It goes on and on and on
and as you just heard in that soundbite,
some of these are actually Latino.
It's not all only white
members of the CBP.
What the heck is going on in your view?
- Well anytime you give
one group of people
authority over another group of people
you run the risk that
the people with authority
are gonna see themselves as above
or better than the people
who they have authority over.
And the way you mitigate
that in a democracy
is you say, well these
people are public servants.
They are actually employed by the public,
they don't lord over the public.
And the problem with that is that
if you create a culture of impunity
where public servants who
have that kind of authority
particularly the authority
over life and death
are never held accountable
when they abuse that authority,
then they begin to
rationalize those abuses
as somehow justified or necessary.
And I think that that's
what we're seeing here
particularly with the Trump administration
imposing policies that are cruel beyond
what we've seen in
previous administrations
even when those administrations
have been strict
on immigration enforcement.
And the people who
carry out those policies
have to be able to figure out a way
to justify what they're doing
and one way that they do that
is by denying the humanity of the people
that they have authority over.
- Yeah you know, the
dehumanization of these folks,
it did remind me, Chris
Hayes put up a post
and it brings back the memories of the way
people treated others
during the invasion of Iraq.
The sense of, these aren't even people.
Or in our own past, the way that people
were able to treat others,
whether it's from enslavement on
but they're just not people
so we don't have to think
of them as human beings.
You have this Customs and
Border protection spokesperson
saying this does not
reflect the values of CBP.
How can that even be true?
They're two different groups,
where people are making this
kinds of mockeries, Maya.
- Yeah, it's clearly not true.
I think assuming all
these posts are accurate
but we have no reason
to believe they aren't
because there was a 2018 exposure,
the Facebook groups existed in 2018
and I think part of the problem
here exactly what Adam said
is the leadership has to say,
not only is this not who
we are as an institution,
it is not what we will
tolerate as managers.
And that's critically important.
If you don't take action
where you have the authority
to take action against employees.
In this case there is an ability
to take disciplinary action,
if there's inappropriate
social media activity.
You have to balance that
with First Amendment Rights
of course, but here the question is,
people who have the
ability, who are armed,
who can actually violate the
human rights of other people
must be held to account,
when they're essentially
dehumanizing in a way,
that really undermines the
effectiveness of the agency
which is supposed to be impartial.
Remember that people coming to the border
have a lawful right based
in international law
as well as US law to seek asylum
and the dehumanization is both offensive
but it also fundamentally undermines
the role that they are
to play at the border
and we should be very
concerned about that.
- I think I quote you every week Adam.
The cruelty is the point.
Like that's why they're doing it.
His base wants to see this.
And so he's showing them
that he can dehumanize them.
Isn't that message coming
from the White House?
That essentially you don't
have to treat these people
like human beings, who cares?
- I do think the message is
coming from the White House
that these people are
not real human beings
and you don't have to treat them properly.
I will say though, that
when it comes to children
that the administration is very aware
that its policies are at
their political weakest point
when people see these images
of children being abused
or being held in dehumanizing conditions.
With the adults it's a little different.
The president likes to brag about
how he's gonna deport a million people
and they're gonna do a
crackdown and all that stuff.
But when it comes to the children,
I actually think they recognize
that this is damaging for them
among everyone but the most
hardcore Trump supporters
who would defend anything
the president did
no matter how horrendous.
- Yeah, but they're not
doing anything about it Maya.
That doesn't mean that
they're changing it.
They won't let these kids go.
That is the thing that
keeps striking me Maya,
they wot let them go.
They're holding them for
almost 60 days in some point,
they just won't let them go.
- They won't let them go.
- If they see that it's wrong,
why don't they let 'em go?
- They won't let them
go and they're actually,
remember we have that
astounding appearance in court
where they were in violation
of the settlement agreement
and said, oh well, we don't
even have to provide soap.
- Yeah, and they moved
them to another facility
because they knew that
the cameras were coming,
mocked the members of Congress
in front of the
supervisors who did nothing
and then moved the kids right back in.
If they really believe that,
if they say they're gonna deport
they're not even doing
that, anyway it's insane.
Anyway, Maya will be right back.
Adam Serwer thank you very much.
I really appreciate and
I'll keep on quoting you.
More AM Joy after the break.
- I like to plan my activities
before I take a trip.
So by the time I get there,
I can just enjoy the ride.
With TripAdvisor, it's easy to discover
over 100000 bookable things to do.
From walking tours in Rome,
to wine tastings in Tuscany.
And if you like what you see,
you can book it with ease.
Just another way TripAdvisor helps you
make your trip a masterpiece.
Read reviews, check hotel
prices, book things to do.
TripAdvisor!
- [Announcer] Are you dermaplaning yet?
- Your skin is just so
much smoother and clearer
and make up goes on perfectly.
- My skin looks younger and healthier.
- My skin is instantly brighter.
It's amazing.
- [Announcer] Now you can
bring professional-style
dermaplaning into your home.
With flawless Dermaplane Glo.
The new exfoliating device
from Finishing Touch
that instantly transforms your skin
to a a more radiant younger
looking complexion in minutes.
Flawless Dermaplane Glo,
instantly and painlessly
removes the top layer of dry dead skin
to reveal brighter, smoother,
younger looking skin
the very first time you use it.
- Dermaplaning is the
most popular treatment
that my clients request.
The moment they get it, they are hooked.
You just can't get enough.
I love the Dermaplane Glo.
It's very user-friendly,
gives like a really
radiant dewy glow to the skin.
- I can't stop touching my face.
- [Announcer] An easy
to use contour design.
A professional-grade exfoliating edge
with safety guard.
And just like a professional treatment,
a built-in LED light, so
you never miss a spot.
- It's very easy to do.
- [Announcer] It's gentle
on all skin types and tones.
Your makeup will never look flawless
if it's sitting on top of
dead skin and peach fuzz
but Dermaplane Glo exfoliates that layer
to create a smooth surface
for creams and makeup.
- My makeup just glides on.
Even my moisturizer,
my skin care products,
they go on easier.
- The Dermaplane Glo transforms my skin
from dull to radiant and glowing.
It gets rid of all the dead skin cells,
all of the peach fuzz and basically
gives you brand new skin.
- [Announcer] Get your
flawless Dermaplane Glo,
including exfoliating
heads for easy replacement.
Go online now at DermaplaneGlo.com.
For only $19.99, with a
60-day money back guarantee.
Or call 1-800-652-8409.
Order right now, and
your shipping is free.
- It's unbelievable,
I'm glowing right now.
- [Announcer] Flawless Dermaplane Glo,
brighter more youthful--
- Do you want me to go first,
or do you wanna go first?
- You can go first.
- Audible reintroduced
this whole world to me.
- So many great stories
from amazing people
makes me wanna be better.
- To be able to connect
with the people's stories
that I'm listening to,
that's an inspiration.
- It's on during my commute,
it's on all the time.
- Doing the dishes.
- Working out.
- On in the car.
- At bed time.
- An Audible listener is someone
that wants to broaden their mind.
- [Woman] People who
are tired of listening
to their radio or music.
- To hear her speak those words--
- It was--
- It was incredible.
- Unbelievable!
- With Audible Originals,
there's something
for almost for every taste in there.
- Everything you ever wanted to hear.
- Well, I signed up for
getting a credit every month
and I started exploring books
that I normally wouldn't read.
- Our ability to empathize
through these stories,
with these stories can
be transformational.
- It's my own thing that I can do for me.
- [Announcer] See what listening
to Audible can do for you.
Just text LISTEN14 to 500500.
(soft music)
- [Announcer] Download
the TouchNote app now.
(dramatic music)
- I know predators and we have a predator
living in the White House.
(crowd cheering)
And the thing about
predators you should know
is that they prey on the vulnerable.
They prey on those who they
do not believe are strong.
- Welcome back to AM Joy.
We're almost three years
after Hillary Clinton
became the first woman
presidential nominee
of a major US political party.
We now have six women running
for president in 2020.
Among the, Senator Kamala Harris,
who along with calling
Donald Trump a predator,
shared exactly why she says
that she has the credibility
to take him down.
- I've had a lot of fights,
most which I've won.
I know how to fight and let me tell you,
we're gonna also need somebody
who can successfully prosecute the case
against another four years
of that administration.
I know how to do that.
- Senator Harris, along with
Senator Elizabeth Warren
saw their stocks soar
in new national polls,
after the first presidential debates.
A Quinnipiac poll that
was released just Tuesday
showed Harris surging 13 points
since last month into second place,
only two points behind
front runner Joe Biden.
That after Harris challenged Biden
over his comments about
working with segregationist
senators and his opposition
to federally mandated busing
in the 1970s.
When asked which candidate
did the best job at the debate
47% said Harris, and she was followed
by Senator Elizabeth Warren with 17%.
Only 6% said that former
vice president Biden
had the best performance.
And when asked which candidate
has the best policy ideas,
Warren took the lead with 31%
compared to 19% in April.
Sanders came in at 18%
while Biden received 11%
a drop from 23 in April.
Now despite these numbers Biden remains
the nominal front runner, even if barely
and the changes in the
standings in the race
are re-upping the question
of whether America
is finally, finally ready
to elect a woman president.
There are now six options, most of them
more politically experienced
and savvy than Trump.
So if not now then when.
Maya Wiley of The New
School is back with me.
Also joining new is Rashad Robinson
of Color of Change.
Tiffany Cross of The Beat DC
and Dean Obeidallah, host
of the Dean Obeidallah Show
on SiriusXM.
I'm gonna go to you first Rashad,
glad I just ran into you last night,
watching Missy Elliott here (laughs)
at the Essence Festival
25th Anniversary, hey!
And so I'm wondering if you had a chance.
I don't know when you got here
but I don't know if you've
had a chance to walk around
and have conversations with people
that you're running into
down here at Essence.
Tell me what you're hearing.
Is the Kamala boom
resonating in the real world
or is this just us people
who are obsessed with polls?
- I think it's a mix of both.
I think it's one, it is people
that are obsessed with polls
and those of us in the political class
who follow these things,
are sort of deeply invested
in looking at the
upticks and the downticks
but people are coming to understand
who Kamala Harris is,
and understanding her track record.
And paying closer attention to us
and that's the power of these debates.
I also am hearing Elizabeth
warren's name a lot.
From a number of people as I walk around
and particularly the way
that she's rolled out
a set of plans and exactly
how she's talking about
how she's going to close some of the gaps
that have plagued communities for so long.
I do think it's just incredibly early
and even the sort of ticks
and hits that Biden has taken
to his polls is a recognition that,
many of his early numbers,
were just that people knew who he was.
It's like going into
a store, a supermarket
and you pick the product off the shelf
that you've seen the most commercials for,
that you know you have
the most attention to
but over time you might change that
as you learn more things.
And so I do think that
it's just really early
but I do think that these debates
are shifting the landscape
and giving people
more on opportunity to see
candidates in a different way.
- Yeah, and that's a
very good point Tiffany
because there is a certain huge advantage
that Biden had just because
people knew who he is.
And people didn't know who a
lot of these candidates were
until like 23 million people
watched that second debate
and said, oh she's interesting.
I wonder if you think that
there's also a potential though
that's it's a little deeper
and that it might be more like 2008.
Where people didn't really know
who Barack Obama was either
but when they saw him in comparison
and realized that he was plausible.
I mean, look at these numbers,
Biden is now only two points
ahead in this latest polls.
Right, in Quinnipiac.
She's only tow points down from him.
Warren is right up there.
She's passed Bernie Sanders, is now at 14,
statistically tied but
one point ahead of him.
She's gone up 13, Harris.
Biden's gone down eight.
It looks like she's
taking that lead from him
and I wonder if he's maybe
a bit too comfortable
assuming I'm the guy black voters like.
But if you even look
among African-Americans,
here's that next poll,
she's only you know,
four points down among African-Americans.
It's a huge change.
It feels a little bit like Barack Obama
versus Hillary Clinton in that '08 primary
or am I reading too much into it, Tiffany?
- Oh well, first let me
say I have serious FOMO
that all you guys are
at the Essence Festival
and I'm missing out.
I don't wanna hear about Missy Elliott,
I'm not there, I have
FOMO, I don't like it.
(loud laughter)
But, back to the issue at
hand, back to the point.
I think a lot of the, so many people
put how they feel about these candidates
through the lens of cable news networks.
And so when you have people offering
analysis and how they
feel even after debate,
a lot of times that conversation is driven
by a media lacking in diversity.
Ethnic diversity, diversity of thoughts,
socioeconomic diversity and so people
tend to look through this very myopic lens
about debate performances.
Even the conversations
that follow the debates,
it became again all
about Elizabeth Warren,
Kamala Harris and Joe Biden.
We forget that Julian Castro
had an amazing performance.
He's a very overlooked candidate I think.
So I think we have to
look at this full scope
to Rashad's point, it is still
very early in the process.
You and I talk about this a lot Joy.
You know how I feel about the polls.
You have to consider, polls are mostly
older Americans, people
who answer landlines.
People who answer landlines
from an unidentified caller.
You're not gonna have a
lot of people doing that
and we have to disaggregate the data.
Look, I think Kamala Harris
is a very electable candidate.
There are other members
in this very crowded slate
who are electable and the American people
will ultimately say yeah.
Ultimately you can't put all your credence
into what polls are saying
and what media analysts even say.
And so we have to, there's
another debate coming up
at the end of July.
We have to look at this in a more,
I think wider lens than
what sometimes offered
in some of these mainstream outlets.
- I agree with you 'cause we
talk about this all the time
but I have to say and I'm
gonna go to Dean on this
because here's the challenge.
Everything that Tiffany just said is true.
But, most people don't have time
to follow all this stuff.
They don't have time
to follow all the polls
so they look at the polls, they
listen to us talk about it.
You talk about the great debate
that Julian Castro had, he
didn't move in the polls
and so then it feeds on itself.
And so that next debate comes around
and he had a great debate
but he didn't move.
And so the thing is
people are trying to think
I gotta narrow these 800
people down to like four.
Right, they gotta stop thinking
about it as four or five,
instead of 40.
The next debate, do you think
maybe the Democratic Party
ought to narrow it down a little bit?
It would eliminate somebody
who's not polling very
high like Julian Castro
who had a contribution to make
but do you think it's bad,
for us to now do another
23 people in the debate.
- I think let this July debates,
it's basically set right now, go forward.
The next debate, September,
already the field is smaller.
But look, this is going to be a battle.
Donald Trump talked about
it on the 4th of July.
Like when the Revolutionary
Army took the airports,
this that kind of battle
we're talking about.
The battle of LaGuardia, en route to JFK.
This is the kind of
fight we're talking about
that's gonna happen between now
and November 2020.
But internally in Democratic Party,
things are gonna change,
they're gonna move.
People want someone to win.
My listeners who call my show,
there are three factors they want
in a Democratic nominee.
Who can beat Trump, who can beat Trump
and who can beat Trump.
That is the key and they say every time,
vote blue no matter who.
So they'll say whoever
I'm supporting is fine.
I'm gonna fight for that person
but we're gonna unite and
win against Donald Trump.
But the more polls you see
where Senator Harris can beat Trump,
the more polls you see where
Senator Warren can beat Trump,
and not just Biden can beat Trump.
It makes them more electable,
and I think undercuts
the idea that Joe Biden
is the only one electable.
And the more that happens,
I think the more Joe
Biden potentially slides.
He could still be the nominee,
but potentially slides.
- Putting aside the fact
that Dean Obeidallah
brought up the battle in
which George Washington
used his fighter planes to
bomb the British front line
during that first battle
to take over the airports
during the Revolutionary War,
we're gonna put that aside for a moment.
We're gonna come back to
politics for a minute Maya Wiley,
because the other issue here too
is that because as Dean said,
it's been seen as Biden's the only one
who can beat Trump.
Because there has been this idea
even among African-Americans
that it's gotta be a white guy.
It's the only guy who can beat Trump.
But when you see her beat him in a debate,
doesn't that make people kinda wonder
well wait a minute, if he can't beat her
maybe this woman actually is the one
who can take Donald Trump down.
- Yeah, I think that's right.
I think one of the things
that's happening here is,
this is sort of a national trauma
around Donald Trump having
won the 2016 election.
Remember that Hillary Clinton did win
by almost three million votes.
Then what she lost was
the electoral college
and she lost that by basically
three states in the Midwest.
It was Pennsylvania,
Wisconsin and Michigan
and so that's where the,
oh we-need-a-white-man fear
comes from, but I also think the fact that
voters voted for Donald Trump
despite his overt sexism
is part of why we are starting to hear
what I think is a very dangerous debate
about is a woman electable?
And what we don't talk,
as much about is, is a
black woman electable?
Because I think part of what's happening
is this notion that the
only way we win the office
is by actually sacrificing who we are
when all of the fundamentals
show that absolutely women
and women of all races are electable.
That's what 2018 taught us
and back to your earlier
point Joy about Barack Obama,
once he won the Iowa caucuses,
he was way behind Hillary
Clinton in the polls, way behind.
When he beat her by
what, about eight points
in the Iowa caucus in '08,
suddenly he was electable.
So I think, it is early,
I agree with everything
everyone else has said, I
think we have to address
the fact that our fear
could be our worst enemy.
In terms of getting the kind of leader
we need for the country.
- Can I tap into that and just say Joy,
just really quickly to Maya's point.
I think she's right, that some people
voted for Donald Trump
despite these things
but we also have to reconcile
with the fact that a lot of people
voted for this president
because of these things
and we still see a lot of ugly rhetoric
coming out of the right
and we have to remember,
these guys are not running
against Donald Trump right now.
They're running against each other
and so we have to get through a primary.
So I take Dean's point, that yeah,
obviously Kamala Harris is electable
and it is something that
voters should pay attention to.
She handled Joe Biden on that stage
and whether you're a
supporter of hers or not,
I think there is this underbelly of people
who are just really dying to see her
body Donald Trump on a debate stage
and dying to see her slap him
around on the debate stage
which she could probably handle very well,
probably better than some
of the other candidates.
But, who's doing the asking?
Who's saying, is a woman electable?
Who's saying is a black woman electable?
And when you look at the people
who are questioning that
they frequently don't look
like some of us on the panel.
So I think, and sometimes they do.
Sometimes there are people
out of South Carolina
who really do think that
black people can be,
we can question ourselves in a way
that sometimes not even
white people question.
- Yeah, I mean to Tiffany's--
- And to add to that point,
go on, go on, go on!
- Yeah I mean to Tiffany's point
which I think is excellent,
that's why this has to be
about expanding the base.
Expanding the electorate.
Not about how many Trump
voters can be peeled off.
But where are the '08
and 2012 Obama voters?
And that means this conversation
that oftentimes the
political class talks about
with low-propensity voters
but we like to talk about
as high-potential voters.
The black folks and the people of color
and young people who oftentimes
never get talked to.
Who is gonna inspire
those voters to turn out?
Because if actually we can
expand the base of voters
and turn out people that have otherwise
not turned out in the last election
and don't turn out
oftentimes in elections,
we not only win elections, but
we win with the type of base
that allows us govern in progressive ways.
To pass the type of legislation
and the type of policy and practice change
that these candidates are
actually talking about.
And so to the point of
both the conversation
about who's having this
conversation in the media
and how the media is covering this
but also who these
candidates are talking to.
This has to be a story
about not just appealing
to the lowest common denominator
but appealing to the aspirations
and expanding the base of voters
and that's why new voices
and voices that are unafraid,
women people of color
are gonna be so important
to usher in the Democratic
Party into the next phase.
- Yeah absolutely, Democratic
Party has to decide
that they have to sort of,
do a sort of kind of a
nostalgia version of themselves
in order to mollify a
certain kind of voter
or do they go forward, I don't know.
The women seem to be
leading that conversation
at the moment, Maya
Wiley, Rashad Robinson,
thank you very much.
Tiffany and Dean, we'll be right back.
And coming up, we're gonna talk Biden
and whether this past week was a glitch
or was it the first hole that the iceberg
ripped into the side of
the Titanic, that's next.
- [Announcer] Thanks Golden Corral.
Dan gets a slow-smoked sirloin.
And my little trio are as
happy as shrimp, oops clams.
And mum got it all,
hook, line and sirloin.
The slow-smoked sirloin and shrimp trio.
Golden Corral, the only one for everyone.
- [Announcer] Alice loves
the scent of Gain so much,
she wish they came in
a fabric softener too.
Say hello to your fairy godmother Alice.
Oh and look they've got Gain scent beads
and drier sheets too.
- Most home owners draw a blank
when asked what their
home projects should cost.
That's why at HomeAdvisor, you can see
what others paid for
similar jobs in your area.
Start your next home project
knowing what you should pay.
Go to HomeAdvisor.com or
download the free app.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Introducing
the Blackstone griddle.
Outdoor cooking without the compromise.
Log on now to Blackstoneproducts.com.
♪ Imagine me in you ♪
♪ And you and me ♪
♪ So happy together ♪
♪ I can't see me lovin' nobody but you ♪
♪ For all my life ♪
- [Announcer] Parents have a
way of imagining the worst.
Especially when your easily
distracted teenager has the car.
At Subaru, we're taking
on distracted driving
with sensors that alert you
when your eyes are off the road.
The all new Subaru Forrester,
the safest Forrester ever.
- [Announcer] On INSP Channel 364,
the summer,
- Let's make some music.
- [Announcer] Belongs to The Duke.
- Drawing quite a crowd.
- [Announcer] Tomorrow at
two, against impossible odds,
they'll uphold the law.
John Wayne, Dean Martin, Ricky Nelson
and Angie Dickinson star.
- Get him in the throat.
And you do the same.
- [Announcer] "Rio Bravo",
tomorrow at 2:00 p.m.
John Wayne movies all month long.
Don't miss The Duke Days of Summer.
- Come and get it boys.
- [Announcer] On INSP Channel 364.
- [Announcer] Get ready
for this summer's biggest
turbo-charged blockbuster.
- You're ready buddy?
- [Announcer] Battle of the 80s super cars
with David Hasselhoff featuring
a race between The Hoff,
Erik Estrada and Dirk Benedict.
Evel Live 2, with Axell
Hodges, Vicki Golden.
Plus Chuck Norris' epic
guide to military vehicles.
- Horsepower and firepower.
- [Announcer] Car week begins
tomorrow at eight on History.
- [Announcer] Visit casper.com today.
- In America, every car is a
Declaration of Independence.
Especially at Daytona.
Just starting the car is
an uprising, a revolution.
It's a time machine to
the front tier days,
good times and a day out for fun
for free Americans
anywhere and everywhere.
And to celebrate our nation's birthday,
we'll do it at Daytona.
And a 200 mile an hour
glory of red white and blue.
(dramatic music)
- I was prepared for them to come after me
but I wasn't prepared for
the person coming at me
the way she came at, she
knew Beau, she knows me.
- It was the most dramatic breakout moment
of the first Democratic debate.
Senator Kamala Harris,
the only black candidate
on the Democratic debate stage,
confronting former vice
president Joe Biden
for boasting about working
with notoriously racist
segregationist senators in past decades
and for his stance on busing,
as a means of integrating
the public school system.
On Friday, Biden did an interview on CNN
trying to clean up on aisle six.
- I think if you take a look,
our positions aren't any
different as we're finding out.
- You were not in favor of busing.
It was a different time, there
were different applications.
Why not just own it and say--
- Oh by the way, here's the thing--
- I was against it, but now I've changed.
- I was in favor of busing
that was de jure busing.
Look, the question is how
do you equalize education
in every area?
And I put forward the most
aggressive plan to do that
and I've been pushing it for a long time.
- Tiffany Cross and Dean
Obeidallah are back with me.
And now joining is Will Bunch
of the Philadelphia Inquirer
and Will I want to talk to you about this
because Biden is now being
compared to Jeb Bush.
Gail Collins wrote a piece
in which she said that Biden,
she worried that he would
prove to be the Jeb Bush
of the 2020 cycle.
On Thursday he seemed
uncertain, unprepared,
and I think this was a
bit cold, she said feeble,
it undermines the core
promise of his candidacy
which is that he's the
guy who can beat Trump.
Another performance like
this one and he's done
but I think more importantly,
what you're seeing from Biden
is that he does seem to be a candidate
geared toward the past.
He's saying I'm gonna
bring the past you liked
which is the Obama era.
He doesn't feel like a
candidate of the future.
Is that a problem for him in this race?
- I think so, absolutely.
I was at his announcement in Philadelphia
and I thought people were
partying like it was 2015.
He wants to go back to the
near past, to the Obama years.
And I think after
everything that's happened
the last three or four years,
I think people are looking
for a new direction forward.
I have to say in that soundbite you played
where he said he wasn't expecting
the Kamala Harris moment.
That's really surprising to me.
He's really had 40
years to prepare for it.
He could tell a good
story about his evolution
on Civil Rights up to the point
where he became the vice president
to the first black
president in this country
and he really fumbled the answer
to where he was mumbling
something about states rights
which, it reminded me of the launch
of Ronald Reagan's 1980
campaign in Mississippi.
And I think the broader problem though is,
Joe Biden has been on the defensive
since the day he entered this race.
And I think Democratic voters
are really looking for affirmative reasons
to support a candidate.
And I think that's why you
were seeing Elizabeth Warren
rise so much in the polls
because she's put out plan after plan
and become a hashtag,
I have a plan for that.
And Biden really hasn't countered that
with any plans or policies
that, I know he has some
but they haven't really
captured the public imagination.
And, last night there
was a new video of him
that was making the rounds
where a voter in Iowa
confronted him about what he was gonna do
about Brett Kavanaugh
in the Supreme Court.
And he basically spent 90 seconds
telling her he didn't have
a plan for that either.
And that's a tough issue.
A lot of the candidates don't have
a good answer for that, I think.
But I think, again and again,
if you're going to see Joe Biden
either trying to defend his past record
or trying to justify his candidacy
beyond just he thinks he
can beat Donald Trump,
you're gonna see him continue
to erode in the polls
if that's his style and
that's the way he campaigns.
- Yeah, I mean Tiffany there's
something about even that.
The thing that Will just mentioned,
about him saying that,
he also said he'd
nominate Merrick Garland,
which is also going backwards
and saying I'm gonna go get that guy
who's like a sort of moderate,
that even when President
Obama nominated him,
people sort of shrugged
until Mitch McConnell said no to him.
Does Biden, and listen, the reality is,
Democrats love Joe Biden.
Let's just be honest,
Democrats love Uncle Joe,
but is that enough of a reason
to nominate him to be president?
Does he need a forward looking strategy
that isn't just you
love me, I'm Uncle Joe.
- And if voters are concerned,
we wanna vote for the person,
who can beat Donald Trump,
if Joe Biden was not prepared
for this moment on busing,
what will he not be prepared for
when he's on the debate
stage with Donald Trump?
And this is a legitimate question
that people have to ask themselves.
And listen, it is not
enough in today's society
in a post-Trump America for you to say,
no, no, no but wait, my
best friend was black,
I served the first black president
and let me go through
this clumsy explanation
on how I came to some of
these policy positions.
That is not going to resonate with voters
particularly, we saw in the midterms
this surge in younger voters
who were younger people during
the Obama administration
who are paying more attention
in this legislative environment now.
Some people's political positions.
So, I think he has a lot of work to do
to resonate with voters and
you have to also look like,
we know some of the people
who work on Joe Biden's staff.
It's like nobody, did you all
not have during debate prep
did you not think that
question would come up?
And why this topic is even being discussed
in the first place, is because
he started out by saying
listen guys, I can work
with segregationists.
I can work with white supremacists
because I've done it before.
And I don't think a lot of
people are looking for you
to work with these people.
People are looking for you
to get these people out root and stem
and redefine what this
government should be
and could be for all people
including people of color
who've been disenfranchised for decades.
- Yeah, and let me play
you what Biden said.
Dean I wanna play this for you.
This is Joe Biden talking on CNN
when he did this
interview with Chris Cuomo
about that moment with Kamala Harris.
- I think it'd be great
to have a female VP.
And if I don't win it'd be great
to have a female president.
- Do you think a Democrat ticket can win
without a woman in one of the two slots?
- Yeah well, the answer is yes,
but I think it helps having
a woman on the ticket.
And there's a lot of really
qualified women out there.
- So that makes the point a little bit
because it does talk about him saying,
yeah, it'd be great to have a female VP.
Again saying maybe in the future,
it'd be great to have a
woman VP and eventually
but here's now, this cut
one from my producers.
This is him actually speaking about
how he felt about being
confronted by Kamala Harris.
This is cut one.
- It was hurtful to hear you
talk about the reputations
of two United States senators
who built their reputations
and career on the segregation
of race in this country.
And it was not only
that but you also worked
with them to oppose busing.
- Sorry about that, okay
I didn't have the cut
that I was looking for.
The one I wanted to play for you,
and I'll just describe it to you Dean.
Is that he says to Chris Cuomo,
that it was hurtful to him
to be confronted that way
by Kamala Harris.
He said, "She knows my
son, she knows my family."
Something about that, I
think as a person of color
maybe hearing it, it
feels like he feels like
he's done so much.
I don't know, it felt as if he felt
that he shouldn't be questioned in a sense
because he's been Barack Obama's VP,
that he shouldn't be questioned.
- Well on some level to me,
and that could be part of it,
it hearkens back to what
we were talking about.
Joe Biden is a throwback
to a different time
where you like someone in
politics, they won't attack you.
They're my friend.
And to remind people, 2016,
in the California primary for Senate,
President Obama and Joe
Biden supported Kamala Harris
in that primary and he campaigned for her.
And so he knows his son as well,
so he was stunned that
someone who is my friend
on the stage, in front of
everyone would mock me.
And that goes back,
criticize me based on policy
and I think that goes back
to an older view of
politics frankly where,
hey we're all friends.
We're only slightly different
from each on policy.
We can all get along
and that's not gonna work
any more today in 2020.
I think Joe Biden time and time again
reminds us of why in 2008,
he got less than 1% of the vote in Iowa
before he dropped out of the race.
He was not a great candidate.
He may have been a great vice
president, I think he was.
He might know the policies inside and out.
As a candidate he's not proving himself
and we need someone truly
that's gonna inspire
people to go in the rain
and knock on doors, to drive
their friends to the polls,
to make phone calls, to donate money.
And Joe Biden is gonna pick up his game
to be that person.
It's just not gonna work,
I was the vice president,
I'm inevitable, give me this position.
Not gonna happen in 2020,
I can assure you that
he still could be the nominee
but it's not inevitable.
That's changed the game
from the first debate.
- Will very quickly,
last word to you on this.
Is Biden running too much
on saying essentially
that he wants to be the president,
does he need to make a clear reason
why he wants to be a president
other than what he's done in the past?
Because it does feel like his candidacy
really is rooted in a
thing where he's like
I've done all this for you in the past,
now it's time for me to be president.
'cause it doesn't sound
like a real strong,
I don't know, what do you think?
- Are you asking me Joy?
- Well people are--
- The reality, I'm sorry.
- People know,
yeah people know--
- [Joy] For will, for Will sorry.
- Yeah that's okay.
If people wanna know
what he's going to do,
also in his announcement, he says
you wanna do something
about climate change,
beat Donald Trump, that's
how you do something
about climate change.
And on one level of course that's right,
but I think people wanna hear much more.
You have other candidates like Jay Inslee
with much more detailed plans
and when he talks about Merrick Garland,
Merrick Garland is a perfect reminder
of why the congenial
approach from the 1970s,
that he wants to bring back,
just isn't gonna work in the 21st century.
How could somebody who was
there for Merrick Garland
and what Mitch McConnell did to him,
think that he can get along
with Republicans anyway.
They had a policy of eight years
of trying to not get anything for Obama,
to deny him a second term and then
to deny him a Supreme Court seat.
And why that would suddenly change
with the installation of
Joe Biden as president,
I just don't see that at all.
- Yeah, I'm not sure that you
can beat massive resistance
with committee, it's hard.
It's a hard argument to make.
Dean and Tiffany will be
back later in the show.
Will Bunch, welcome to this show,
we'll have you back on
again, thank you very much.
And coming up, after multiple indictments,
over 10000 lies and bowing
to dictators across the globe
Donald Trump has seen exactly
one elected Republican
quit their party.
Justin Amash's Independence Day, next.
(dramatic music)
- When you're volunteering,
you never hear it's not my job.
That's because right where you live
there's a need for your time and skills
and effort and talent.
Please consider volunteering
and feeling that feeling
that you helped someone today.
The More You Know.
- [Announcer] Play it cool
and escape heartburn fast,
with new TUMS Chewy
Bites cooling sensation.
♪ Tum tum tum tum tums ♪
- [Announcer] Pain, swelling, stiffness.
When your hands hurt, you
can't function, until now.
Introducing the new Copper
Fit compression gloves
with sure grip technology,
to give you more power, more control
and more agility than ever.
Our most advanced, copper-infused
compression fabric,
woven into an ultra
lightweight performance glove
that fits like a second skin.
To support relief and
recovery of sore muscles
and painful joint stiffness.
And new sure grip bands built in
to provide a strong non-slip grip
for more power and control.
- You need total control of your hands
when you're doing anything
with construction.
Your hands are your livelihood.
The Copper Fit gloves are great,
the grip is outstanding here
with this different ribs.
It makes my hand a lot more usable.
It just feels like you're just ready
to start the job.
- The gloves have been
a gamechanger for me.
They help with flexibility
and pain and soreness.
They allow me to do my job even better.
- [Announcer] Breathable wicking fabric
with an open finger design
for full range of
motion, feel and control.
- They relieve my pain.
When I grab something I'm not in pain.
The support or whatever
magic these things do,
I don't know what it is.
It doesn't matter to me
what it is, it works.
- I get a lot of pain and
it can make it difficult
to do the smallest thing.
While I'm wearing this,
I do not have any pain.
I can use it on a keyboard,
I can use my phone,
I drive with it, I sleep
with it, I love this glove.
- [Announcer] The new Copper
Fit compression gloves
with sure grip technology.
Relief from painful,
muscle and joint soreness.
Guaranteed or your money back.
Call 1-800-258-3808,
or on the web at
getcopperfitgloves.com for only $19.99.
Order right now and your shipping is free.
- I've tried it, I use
it, I know it works.
- Copper Fit gloves definitely
just make my life better.
- I've used Copper Fit before.
This has helped my hands so much.
These things work.
- [Announcer] Feel better with
copper infused compression.
Ask for it by name.
Copper Fit compression gloves.
- [Announcer] Paul, you're
the greatest neighbor.
You help us find the best
home improvement pros,
get quotes and research
prices for our home projects.
- That, that's not me.
That's HomeAdvisor.
- [Announcer] You can't expect your--
(soft music)
- [Announcer] For those
who gaze up at starry skies
and ponder the vastness before them,
asking why, where and how.
This is CuriosityStream,
where you can stream
incredible documentaries
from the best filmmakers
anywhere in the world.
Long live the curious.
- Are you looking for a
trustworthy publishing company
to publish your book.
- Covenant Books is an
author-friendly publisher
who shares your passion and beliefs.
Call us today and we'll send you
a free author packet to
help get you started.
- [Announcer] Call 800-678-3402.
- [Announcer] I bet you've
never seen a bed like this.
It's the new Craftmatic
Legacy, rising pillow rest
adjustable bed, featuring
bedside power plugs,
under-bed night lights and more for less.
Up to 50% less than
Tempur-Pedic, Sleep Number
and other adjustables.
Call now, you gotta see
how little they cost.
(rain pounding down)
(dramatic music)
- Okay, a quick note of host privilege.
I wanna thank everyone who has bought
my brand new book "The
Man Who Sold America:
"Trump and the Unraveling
of the American Story"
This week it officially became
a New York Times best seller
which is super bucket list exciting.
And thank you very much
to all the great folks
that we've met here in New
Orleans at the Essence Fest.
Yesterday, we did a book
signing, it was so much fun.
You can get your copy
wherever books are sold
and maybe I'll come and sign
one near you, where you live.
Coming up, straight up
more AM Joy (laughs)
(dramatic music)
- Pain thinks it makes the rules,
but the rules just changed.
New Icy Hot Lidocaine dry spray.
Instant dry technology,
no mess, no residue,
fast-acting relief.
Rise from pain.
New Icy Hot Lidocaine dry spray.
- [Announcer] Have you ever
seen something so beautiful
that all you could say was wow!
Or walked on the world's best beach?
At a place that made you feel
like you were in a dream?
Where family comes first?
And fun is measured one ride at a time.
♪ Hear all about a good life ♪
- [Announcer] Where
you're served like royalty
but treated like family.
Beaches Turks and Caicos,
where anything is possible
because everything is included.
Wow, get up to 65% off.
Call 1-800-Beaches.
- [Announcer] They're coming for you.
They're in your house and
they're out for blood.
There's just nowhere to hide
from the the mosquitoes,
bugs and flies inside.
But now, you can fight
those monsters back,
with the Bell and Howell Monster Trapper.
It's the ultimate bug killer.
No dangerous pesticides, no
high frequencies or sounds
and no sticky flypaper.
The secret is Monster Trapper's UV light
that attracts them so that
3500 RPM Vacuum can trap them.
Monster Trapper traps them in,
then you dump them out.
And the best part is, Monster
Trapper is whisper quiet.
It's silent bug deadly.
Watch in just six hours Monster Trapper
catches hundreds of nasty bugs, amazing!
Monster Trapper traps mosquitoes,
flies, fleas, wasps and more.
There's nowhere bugs can hide,
because they're all trapped
inside the Monster Trapper.
Just plug it in and let
the bug trapping begin.
Use it anywhere in your house,
from the garage, to the
kitchen, to your bedroom.
And because of the unique one-way design,
bugs stay in the trap
until you throw them away.
Look, you wouldn't wear
insect repellent to bed.
So use Monster Trapper instead.
It's so quiet, you won't
even know it's there.
And it's not just for inside.
Use Monster Trapper by the grill
to keep pests off your food.
Keep a Monster Trapper in the RV
to ensure you're camping bug-free.
Or plug it in to trap all those
annoying mosquitoes and flies.
Look, just one visit from the exterminator
can cost over $100.
When it comes to trapping all those pests,
Monster Trapper works best.
During this special TV only offer,
you can get your Monster
Trapper for just $29.99.
Try it for 90 days.
If Monster Trapper doesn't
make your life bug free,
return it for a full-refund
of the purchase price.
But wait, order now and you can get
a second Monster Trapper.
Just pay a separate free.
We'll even ship your entire order free.
Call or go online now.
- [Announcer] To order
call 1-800-957-2316.
That's 1-800-957-2316
or you can order online
at monstertrapper.com.
- [Announcer] Driverless
cars or trips to Mars, $4.95.
Delivery drones or the
latest phones, $4.95.
No matter what you trade,
at Fidelity it's just $4.95
per online US equity trade.
- Isn't this a situation of
hate the game not the player?
- This is a power play.
This is a strategic move from her, right?
- Why is this potentially such a big deal?
- We have more breaking
news, why wouldn't we?
Its Tuesday in Washington.
- The wall is a sticking
point, not border security.
- Although the promise was
a wall paid for by Mexico.
- I cannot wait to keep
talking about 2020.
I gotta tell you, I
think it's fascinating.
- Your entire business is profiting off
of other's people's information.
Then your job, is to keep
that information safe.
(soft music)
(dramatic music)
- I was hoping to set
an example for people.
I've been involved in
party politics for a while
and I believe very strongly
that it's hurting our
country at this point.
And I think people need to
stand up for what's right.
Stand up for what they believe in.
Be independent of these party loyalties
that really divide is.
- That is former and that is right, former
Republican Congressman Justin Amash
on why he decided to leave the party.
Choosing, you guessed it, the 4th of July
to celebrate his independence.
Amash was the only sitting
Republican Member of Congress
to support impeaching Donald Trump.
He explained his decision
to quit the party
entirely in a Washington Post op-ed.
Saying quote, true to
George Washington's fears,
Americans have allowed
government officials
under assertions of
expediency and party unity
to ignore the most basic tenets
of our constitutional order.
Separation of powers,
federalism and the rule of law.
The result has been the consolidation
of political power and
the near-disintegration
of representative
democracy and back with me,
Daily Beast columnist Dean Obeidallah.
Also joining Noelle Nikpour,
Republican strategist
and Jason Johnson, the
Republican Jason Johnson,
not the journalist Jason Johnson
who is the consultant
and former senior advisor
to Senator Ted Cruz, so people don't think
that we introduced the wrong person
'cause there are two of you guys.
All right, so let me go to you first Dean.
The reason I wanted to keep you here
is you actually know this guy.
Tell us a little bit about him,
because he is an interesting character.
Interesting person.
- Well I met him once.
- I shouldn't say character,
interesting Guy.
- We have a lot
of mutual friends.
What I do admire a great deal that
it took the son of a Palestinian refugee
to be the first one to
stand for impeachment
and I said that as the son of
a Palestinian refugee myself,
and when I met him, I was the MC
out of an Arab-American event in DC
where he was being honored years ago
and it wasn't partisan.
But let's be clear about one thing.
Donald Trump called him
a disloyal Republican.
This is a guy, Justin,
who is a founder of the Freedom Caucus.
This is a guy who's got a higher rating
from the American Conservative Union,
higher than Lindsey Graham.
But to Donald Trump it's not about loyalty
to the Republican Party,
or conservative principles,
it's loyalty to one
person, Donald J. Trump.
So, this congressman
refused to be loyal to him.
It's not loyalty to the party.
And Justin's put the constitution
above his party before
and now he's put his party to the side,
said I stand up for the
United States of America
and I'm against partisan politics
that's become toxic, so
I applaud for him that.
- Very quickly, he's
Syrian and Palestinian.
One parent is Syrian--
- I'm only half Arab,
he's 100% Arab.
I'm a 1/2 Arab guy, he's a pure out there.
So I think it's probably
shocked a lot of Republicans.
- And you know Noelle Nikpour,
it used to be, back you know,
I'm old enough to
remember when a plurality
if not a majority of people
who are Arab-American
in particular were Republicans.
Were sort of geared toward
the Republican Party.
There's been a huge exit of the party
by people of that record.
And he's not for that reason,
his piece in the Washington Post
I thought was brilliant.
He really explained where we are
in terms of hyper partisanship
just eroding our politics
and that's really on one side
more than the other to be honest with you.
The Republican Party
said that Barack Obama
essentially doesn't exist as president.
We will make him not exist.
The fact that he's left,
what does it mean and why
is he the only one Noelle?
- Well, you know in my opinion
I think it was a wrong move
that he left the Republican Party
because although he doesn't
like President Donald Trump,
he does respect the platform
of the Republican Party.
In my opinion, you
really can't make change
and you really can't make a
difference if you just quit.
You just quit the party
because you don't like
who's representing the party.
You've got an opportunity
while you're in the party
to get other people to convince them
of making change with policy.
Really the way you make
change is in policy
not by quitting because I know
he's not gonna go on the other side
and join the Democrat party.
So it just leaves him to be an Independent
and the likelihood of
him getting reelected
is probably not good.
So therefore, I wish
that he would have stayed
and made his case and really fought
for what he believed
in and tried to change
the direction of the course
versus just quitting it.
- First of all, it's Democratic Party,
we have to do that, that
is one rule on the show.
We don't use sort of the fake
names the Democratic Party,
we're gonna go with Democratic Party.
I'm gonna go to you Jason,
because the thing that he is,
okay let's say he loves the
tax cuts for the rich, okay.
That he likes the Republican thing.
I don't know he could
like the kids in cages
but maybe let's say he likes that too.
What he specifically has a problem with
is breaking the law.
This guy has been very clear.
He actually read the Mueller report.
He's one of the few in Congress
that's actually read it.
He read it and said oh,
this guy violated 10 times,
the law that if he was a
civilian he'd be in prison
for obstructing justice.
If you can't be for the
president of the United States,
having to actually uphold the law
he swears to uphold I'm not
sure what your purpose is
as a politician.
So doesn't he get credit
for actually believing
enough in the rule of law to say
this guy violated, I'm outta here.
- So Joy, two things.
Number one I'm not going to sit here
and try to argue that Justin Amash's exit
from the Republican Party
and declaring himself an Independent
is detached and has nothing to do
with his calling for
impeachment of the president.
Clearly there's a direct correlation.
At the same time, I
think it's very important
and I know it's tempting
to only get wrapped up
in the Donald Trump portion.
If you read that editorial,
I too thought it was brilliant.
I agreed with almost every
word within that editorial
because the reality is long
before Donald Trump came along,
this hyper partisanship, I mean,
think about what was just
said a moment ago by Noelle.
Why should Justin Amash, a member today
elected by his district of
the House of Representatives
be any less effective in arguing
for his brand of
constitutional conservatism
simply because he doesn't
have an R next to his name?
Now I'm not saying that he
won't be less effective,
in fact he will, but that in of itself,
sort of makes the point with
the problem that we have today.
You either are on team red or team blue
and I think we all know that unfortunately
we listen or we're open-minded
to the arguments presented
based upon the color of
the other person's jersey
and that's unfortunate,
it shouldn't be that way.
- Yeah, and then to that
point Noelle, answer that.
Because it's true, if you're saying
he still believes in the
principles of conservatism
then you mean if he takes off team red,
suddenly he is not a person
who should legitimately be reelected.
If people agree with what he's for
why shouldn't he get
reelected as an Independent?
- Well I mean, I feel like
that we have turned politics
into a bloodsport.
- [Joy] But aren't you doing that,
by saying that if he
takes off the red jersey,
suddenly he can't get
reelected, why shouldn't he?
- Because it's going to
be hard to raise money.
That's number one and if
you have turned your back
on the GOP, he said he
was quitting the GOP,
he didn't say he was
quitting Donald Trump.
He could've said maybe
I'm quitting team Trump.
I don't agree with that. He
said he's quitting the GOP!
- But how do you quit team Trump?
Wait hold on, hold on one second.
Wait a second, Donald Trump is the GOP.
Donald Trump is the head
of the Republican Party.
All of the policies, that Donald
Trump is putting in place,
your party 100% is standing behind him on.
Whether it's the children in cages,
which violates all kinds of laws
and maybe the Geneva Convention.
They're behind him on tariffs,
which are destroying
people's farms and ranches.
Destroying their lives.
They're behind him on everything he does,
even if he's saying I'm going
to ignore the Supreme Court.
If no one has quit over that,
Charlottesville, nothing else,
does the guy get credit for
saying he has some principle.
At some point he says enough.
- He totally gets credit
for being his own man
and standing up for things
that he doesn't believe in or agree with,
but to quit the party.
The Republican Party
platform is not Donald Trump.
It's a platform--
- But it is!
But it is, no yes it is.
It is Donald Trump, it is.
It's 100% Donald Trump.
It's whatever he wants he does it.
Whatever Donald Trump
wants that's the platform.
- But he ran under the GOP label.
But the GOP didn't run on
his label or his brand.
So in effect--
- So then the kids in cages
are the Republican platform?
- Well, I just feel like,
back to the original
point, I just feel like
for him to try to do
a reelection campaign,
raising money, trying to
depend on major GOP donors
to help get his message out,
I think that it's gonna be really hard.
I just don't see him getting reelected
when he quits the
Republican Party, trying to,
what are you gonna run,
I guess you're gonna run as an Independent
and where are you gonna get
the funding sources for that?
There's not a lot of--
- It's all about money.
Let me give Jason the last word.
Jason will there be
more, will there be other
Justin Amash's in your view.
- Well I would assume go forward.
Again, because this started
long before Donald Trump.
We will see more members.
It's amazing, out of 435
elected representatives
in the people's house there
now is only one Independent.
We hear all the time, about
how at least 1/3 of the country
is in fact Independent,
yet there's one out of 435.
Go forward and this
surprised both parties.
Unless the political
parties which are coalitions
of policy demanders, start to respond
to their bases and then
work with one another,
beyond just the brand
on the actual issues,
I do believe we will see more individuals
declaring their Independent
candidacy go forward.
- Last word to you Dean Obeidallah.
If he ran as an Independent,
would Democrats support him?
- They might 'cause they
came out to his town hall--
- Despite his policy differences?
- He got a standing ovation.
But let's be, it's about,
the GOP is about loyalty
to Donald Trump only.
It stands for nothing.
The GOP is Trump and Trump is the GOP.
It's a party, not team
red, it's team Trump.
And not one Republican stood up for Justin
when Trump said he's disloyal.
He's not disloyal to Republican values,
he's disloyal to Donald Trump.
And that dictator-in-chief
demanded he be gone.
- I recommend everybody read,
not Jason Johnson actually,
read Justin Amash's piece
in the Washington Post,
it's quite good.
Dean Obeidallah, Noelle
Nikpour, Jason Johnson,
thank you all very much.
Coming up, the freak out, the freak out
over a teenage mermaid
and what it tells us
about America's culture war, is next.
(dramatic music)
- I found a way to relieve my constipation
that's both gentle and fast.
New Dulcolax liquid works naturally
with the water in my body
to provide gentle relief
in as little as 30 minutes.
New stimulant-free Dulcolax liquid
puts you comfortably in control.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Introducing
the Blackstone griddle.
Outdoor cooking without the compromise.
Log on now to blackstoneproducts.com.
- [Announcer] With tough
food, your dentures
may split and fall.
Fixodent ULTRA Max Hold gives you
the strongest hold ever
to lock your dentures.
So now you can eat tough
food without worry.
Fixodent and forget it.
- I like to plan my activities
before I take a trip.
So by the time I get there,
I can just enjoy the ride.
With TripAdvisor, it's easy to discover
over 100000 bookable things to do.
From walking tours in Rome
to wine tastings in Tuscany.
And if you like what you see,
you can book it with ease.
Just another way TripAdvisor helps you
make your trip a masterpiece.
Read reviews, check hotel
prices, book things to do,
TripAdvisor!
- I have one kid in each
branch of the military.
But I'm Command Central.
- [Announcer] Why Elaine chose Verizon.
- It's so important to us that Verizon
is supporting military families.
When I have a child deployed,
having a reliable
network means everything.
So when I get a video chat
and I get to see their face,
it's the best thing in the world.
And I've earned, every
one of this gray hairs.
Military moms, we serve too.
- [Announcer] The network
more people rely on,
gives you more.
Like military planes with a
special price on unlimited.
$100 per line, and big
savings on our best phones
when you switch, that's Verizon.
- [Announcer] CoQ10 is the
number one cardiologist
recommended supplement for people taking
cholesterol-lowering statin drugs.
Qunol with three times better absorption
than regular CoQ10, has the number one
cardiologist recommended form of CoQ10.
Qunol, the better CoQ10.
- 10 years ago, I had an
undiagnosed heart condition
and erectile dysfunction
was actually the first sign
that something was wrong.
- Luckily I'm a doctor.
An expert in sexual
health, and Zach's dad.
- Not everyone has a doctor in the house
and some health conditions
can be really tough to talk about.
We started Roman to change that.
- Now you can go online
and chat with a physician.
- And if treatment is right for you,
we'll ship genuine medication
right to your door.
- If you're experiencing
ED, hair loss, cold sores
or other issues, let's take care of it.
- Hi!
- [Woman] Look at how great you look.
- Thank you!
- I've been on a diet for
as long as I can remember.
- I even cut out bread
and pasta for a day.
- I decided something needed to change
and then I tried Noom.
- Noom worked for me.
- It's an easy to stick to program
that actually changed my habits.
They say it's based on a
cognitive behavioral approach.
I just say it works.
- It just clicked, it worked.
It worked with Noom.
- [Announcer] Vist noom.com
and lose the weight for good.
- Cover it up, that's what I did
when I started losing my hair.
But then I realized, I
could actually do something.
Now I use Keeps, the
easiest way to keep my hair
and it only costs a dollar a day.
Which means no more covering up.
Get started at keeps.com.
(ominous music)
- [Announcer] Join Hagrid,
and face the forbidden forest
in the epic new addition
to your wizarding world of Harry Potter.
Only at Universal Orlando Resort!
♪ Like a song of love ♪
♪ That clings to me ♪
♪ How the thought of you ♪
♪ Does things to me ♪
♪ Wish that I am unforgettable too ♪
- Voice of Disney's
newest Ariel, Halle Bailey
who is set to star in the live action
Little Mermaid remake.
Well now, here's where you
may wanna have any kids
under 12 leave the room.
I'm gonna give you a
moment, take a moment,
take 'em out of the room.
Okay, so mermaids aren't real.
I know, they're not real.
So in theory, anyone could
play a mermaid, right?
Wrong!
The announcement of Ariel's casting
has caused a multi-day freak out
amongst some Disney fans who are upset
that the actress cast to
play Ariel is not white.
Back with me is Tiffany
Cross of The Beat DC
and joining me now,
entertainment journalist
Chris Witherspoon.
Okay Chris, I gotta go to you first.
Because like, this seemed
like a perfectly adorable
wonderful thing, she is
adorable, the young lady
who's going to play Ariel.
She tweets out dream come true,
animated picture of an
African-American there.
People are excited that you're gonna have
this cute little African-American
girl being Ariel,
but the freak out was real.
Not my Ariel trended,
I think it trended for a couple of days
after this happened and
people were screaming
she's supposed to be white
with red hair, what the H.
What is going on?
- You know, I'm giving
you eye rolls right now
because I was shocked
by the freak out myself
and a lot of the folks
that were freaking out
were white adults who grew
up with Little Mermaid
that came on at like maybe nine.
They had this white
depiction of a princess
that we have seen for decades.
And I think that the
freak out is unwarranted.
The reality is that there have
been 11 Disney princesses.
Guess how many of them
have been black, just one.
So 91% of the sort of depiction
and the narrative of what
it is to be a princess
has been through this white lens.
So it's past due.
And the last time that
we had a black princess
was 10 years ago.
So calm down, have several seats
and let's embrace Halle
and all of her talent.
That clip just showcased, she is fierce.
And she deserves this role, hands down.
- It's interesting...
Let me just read one tweet
and thank you to my team
for putting this up there,
'cause I think this sort of
made the point very well.
This is a woman named Stephanie Renee.
Who says my children
were raised with Ariel.
She's an icon in the eyes of many children
and adults of today, okay.
To change her race is absurd.
That would be like someone making a movie
about Oprah Winfrey
and hiring a white girl
to play Oprah, Oprah is an icon.
We wouldn't want to change her.
Okay, first of all Oprah
Winfrey is a real person
so if you made a movie about her,
you'd want her to look kinda like Oprah.
This isn't a documentary.
There is no such person as Ariel,
it's not a person--
- And there is no time--
- She's just a fictional character.
- There is no time under the sea
where Sebastian says
Ariel and your whiteness
and your Caucasian
experience, it doesn't happen.
So we could easily recreate
and retell this story
however we see fit.
And I think Disney is doing a great job
at being inclusive and
finding ways to tell
diverse narratives and
do colorblind casting.
- It's really interesting.
Tiffany, I'm gonna come to you on this
because when "Malcolm X" was made
and I thought the movie was brilliant
and this was the Spike Lee film,
I had a slight problem,
with just the casting
of Malcolm X, brilliant,
Denzel Washington is a genius,
he can play anything but he's darker skin
and having light skin
was like part of Malcolm X's character.
Like you know what I mean?
So if you look at something like that,
you're saying okay maybe
the casting was odd
because his whole
personality had to partly do
with his complexion.
But this isn't a documentary.
It's about a fictional pretend creature
that's actually a fish.
- And even to the crazy
lady who's tweeting out
the tweet you just read,
how many white people
have actually played real black people?
You have white actors play Michael Jackson
and other people.
How often do our stories get whitewashed
in mainstream Hollywood,
so this is so ridiculous.
Honestly Joy, I have a theory.
I think that not my Ariel
thing trended briefly
because of those fringe
internet section comments
crazy people who tweet
out this ridiculous things
but I think the overwhelming
majority of people
who made this trend, were
people who disagreed,
who were saying how
ridiculous you all sound
saying this is not my Ariel
and this goes back to
the Megyn Kelly comments
that Santa is white.
And we could even look
at the Disney princesses
and they all look the same
even among the white princesses,
they all look the same.
There's never been a disabled princess.
There's never been an overweight princess,
so there are so many
areas where we can grow
and learn in these
spaces and to your point,
it is a cartoon character you idiots,
like what are you upset about?
You sound so ridiculous.
- I never disagree with
anything that Tiffany says
but Santa is real, his name is Larry,
we've had him on the show twice.
So I'm just saying, Santa's real.
Don't play with me with
Santa, 'cause I met him.
- Can I say about Halle Bailey,
this girl is so talented.
Her and her sister they write music,
the understand music, they're
part of the Beyonce family
which you know I'm the honorary president
of the Beyonce fan club--
- Come through, can I be
the vice president?
- So anything she touches is,
well Chris you're my honorary co-chair
of the Beyonce fan club.
- Thank you.
- She's so talented and
if there's one sad thing
to be taken away of this,
it's that her joy was taken away
because of these fringe, crazy people
tweeting these things.
- And I think that the finger pointing,
if there is any in this scenario
it should really go towards Hollywood
and the fact that over the past,
since 1937 and Disney films,
we've seen "Snow White"
and "Cinderella", "Sleeping Beauty"
and they've all kind of looked the same
as you said Tiffany.
So I think it's high time that Hollywood
begins to embrace and open doors
and allow creatives that
have these stories to tell,
they can create new stories.
Maybe it's not gonna be Ariel,
maybe it's gonna be an
actual black princess
who lives in Harlem or Brooklyn.
- Yep, there you go!
- We need to see more
and new stories, or more new stories.
- And by the way the
people sort of overall,
this comes to the overall trauma
that people are feeling about
the changes in the culture
and that the culture doesn't
look like them anymore
that they're not in the center.
This is all a bigger
picture, so we wanna talk
about this today.
- Well we aint going back.
We aint going back.
- 'cause there is a bigger
picture, yes absolutely.
Thank you guys, Tiffany
Cross, Chris Witherspoon,
you guys go have your
meeting about Beyonce,
I'll call into it later?
- We'll Skype you in.
- And coming up
more AM Joy after the break.
(phone buzzing)
- [Announcer] This is your wake up call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis,
month after month, the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion,
HUMIRA can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
HUMIRA targets and blocks
the source of inflammation
that contributes to joint pain,
and irreversible damage.
- [Announcer] HUMIRA
can lower your ability
to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes fatal infections
including tuberculosis and cancers
including lymphoma have happened.
As have blood, liver and
nervous system problems.
Serious allergic reactions
and new or worsening heart failure.
Tell your doctor if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections are common
and if you've had TB, Hepatitis B
or prone to infections or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if
you have an infection.
- [Announcer] Help stop the clock
on further irreversible joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here, right now, HUMIRA!
- [Announcer] Tired of struggling
with regular mirrors that don't adjust
so you can't get close enough?
You need Flexible Mirror, the bendable,
light up magnification
mirror that comes to you.
Just stick it on and turn the base.
The super suction locking mechanism
means you can put it on
any smooth-surfaced place.
Lock it onto any mirror, table or desk.
Even on a window,
the secret is Flexible
Mirror's super strong
articulating arm that's attached
with an ingenious ball and socket
so it can swivel and rotate
for the perfect angle.
The mirror is precision crafted
with 10 times magnification
and crystal clear optics.
You can get Flexible
Mirror for the special
TV discount price of just $19.99.
It comes with our 90-day
no questions asked
money back guarantee and
we give you free shipping
on your entire order.
Here's how to order.
- [Announcer] To order
call 1-800-682-5085.
That's 1-800-682-5085 or order online
at tryflexiblemirror.com.
- [Announcer] What is love?
Two hearts, one soul,
a kiss, a hug, a laugh.
It's passion, it's freedom, it's mystery,
it's the journey and the destination.
It's vows made and promises kept.
It's a feeling, a need, no rules.
All included, all unlimited.
Feed your hunger, quench your thirst,
live your dreams.
Fulfilled, indulged, reborn.
What is love?
Love is all you need.
- [Announcer] Not sure you
have the right credit card,
know which one to get?
Turn to the nerds, dinner's
on me get it (laughs).
The experts at NerdWallet make it easy
to make smart money moves.
Compare and find the
best credit cards for you
at nerdwallet.com.
- [Announcer] Names matter.
Your name, the name
you've made for yourself
and the name of the company you represent.
That's why at 4imprint,
every name and logo
is printed with certainty.
Write the first time on.