- Taste like?
- It's actually really good!
- Is it good?
- I mean--
- Does it taste like meat? (laughs)
- Not really, more bourbon.
- You know what--
- Tastes like bourbon!
- You really taste the bourbon--
- So it's got bits of steak--
- It's dominant.
And bourbon is good.
- Bits of steak.
Swirled bourbon caramel--
- Me likey!
- Char seasoning in
there, so if you like meat
and if you like ice cream--
- They have a little bacon
on top as well.
- It's a stupid thing, man!
- And Ed, thank you for
his marvelous t-shirt--
- I love it!
- Such a great gift.
"World war, win, repeat,
America."
- America.
Come on, join us tomorrow--
- Happy weekend!
See you tomorrow!
- We're gonna have
a lot of fun.
- See ya tomorrow!
(crowd cheers)
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- [Woman] Get under the
table, get under the table!
- Oh (bleep)!
- Oh, my God!
- [Woman] Oh, my God!
- It's happened again, California bracing
with a second earthquake
striking foundations
and roads cracking, fires erupting
and now the fear another
one could be coming
as California Governor Gavin
Newsome declares a state
of emergency in San Bernardino County.
Welcome, everybody, happy weekend,
I'm Neil Cavuto and you're looking live
at Los Angeles International Airport,
where all is calm right now
after a second quake in
as many days strikes north
of the major city, near
Ridgecrest, California
where the first one epicentered.
That's where you'll find our Jeff Paul,
in the middle of it all.
Jeff, how are things there now?
- Yeah, Neil, I would say
there's a general feeling
of uneasiness.
Two days, two big, massive earthquakes,
right here, near this town in California
and this latest one, a magnitude 7.1.
It is followed by several aftershocks,
within just the last few minutes or so
while we were waiting to speak with you,
we felt several of them
out here at city hall.
And that uneasiness is
leading towards many people
just not wanting to sleep
inside their house last night.
In fact, we caught up
with one sheriff's deputy
who told us, while they
were out patrolling,
going street-by-street to
make sure people were okay
and accounted for,
he saw a lot of people
either sleeping outside
or coming here to city hall,
where there is a shelter set up.
Now I want to go to a moment here,
maybe we can pull up the
actual sound on this,
this was the moment we
were at a restaurant.
We started to feel the
rumbling, the violent shaking
and this is what happened right
after that, take a listen.
(metal clanging)
(people exclaiming)
(women scream)
- [Man] Go, go!
- Get out!
- Keep walkin', keep walkin'!
- Everybody out.
- Go, go!
- Keep walkin'!
- [Man] Come one, come on, go!
- Yeah, you could really hear
the panic on people's voices.
This again, was a restaurant
right here in Ridgecrest
and there was a slight
aftershock before this
and everyone sort of, they'd
been through a few of 'em
in the last day.
But then this next one, the 7.1,
the whole building was shaking,
dishes were crashing on the ground
and you could see some
of the people out there,
just walking out in disbelief,
some people hitting the
ground, coming to tears.
And shortly after walking
out of this restaurant
and collecting ourselves, we
look off into the distance
and we see a huge plume of smoke.
We get closer and realize
that this house is on fire
and we do know that this
is at least one house
that was set on fire.
A lot of these fires start
because of ruptured gas lines.
Incredibly, we're only
hearing of some minor injuries
due to broken glass or
things falling on people,
no reports of any deaths,
but the governor here has
declared a state of emergency
and has requested a
presidential declaration
for some help out here from
the Federal Government.
So far, the President hasn't Tweeted about
what's happened here lately in California.
Neil.
- All right, Jeff, thank
you very, very much
and as Jeff pointed out,
the California Governor Gavin Newsome has
already declared a state of emergency
in at least San Bernardino County
as officials assess the
damage, brace for more.
And that's what has
everyone on tenterhooks,
what kind of more does that mean?
How much more, how significant?
On the phone with us is
Public Information Officer
from California Governor's
Office of Emergency Services,
Bryan May.
Bryan, thank you for taking the time.
How are things looking there now?
- [Bryan] Well, we've
been working overnight
since this second earthquake
happened yesterday evening.
Unfortunately for us,
that second earthquake
happened right before sunset,
darkness prevented us from being able
to do a lot of assessment overnight.
We've just had sunrise here in California
in the last hour or so, so
right now is crucial for us,
as we're getting into Ridgecrest
and into the affected areas,
to see what kind of damage
we're talking about.
Injuries, we've heard there are some,
but we're not quite sure how much.
And of course you heard
of people who don't want
to go inside their homes right now.
We need to get in and
see what the needs are
so that we can meet those needs.
- [Neil] Now blessedly,
we've not heard any reports
of significant injuries or
worse, is that still the case?
- [Bryan] Yeah, as of this morning,
and we've been having briefings all night,
we've had crews around the clock here
in the emergency operations
center just outside Sacramento,
we haven't heard of any serious injuries.
We do know that there are some,
but not so much how
serious the injuries are,
so that's again, what we've
gotta do this morning.
We know there've been
hospitals that were evacuated
and as you saw, some of the power lines
and gas lines that are been broken,
so we've gotta get in there today
and find out what we're dealing with.
- [Neil] You know these
aftershocks are more significant
than the main event by a
factor of up to 10 times
and I'm wondering how unusual is that
for Californians who are always braced
for the possibility of this kind of stuff
but not the follow up kind
of stuff they've been seeing?
- [Bryan] Yeah, and I'm
gonna defer to the geologist
that we've been working with,
but in talking with them a
lot over the last 48 hours,
it's not that uncommon.
And now what we're seeing is
that the initial earthquake
that we saw wasn't now
considered the main earthquake,
that was now called a foreshock
because the bigger the earthquake,
that becomes the main one.
So now this 7.1, that
happened yesterday evening,
is the main earthquake
and the one that we felt
on the Fourth of July is now
being called a foreshock.
Again, not that uncommon if you talk
to the geologists that cover these things.
- [Neil] You know,
Bryan, I'm just curious,
we get these anecdotal reports,
I don't know how rampant they are,
a lot of folks afraid
to sleep in their homes
so they're sleeping out on their driveway
or they're sleeping outside,
they're that anxious.
How widespread is that?
- [Bryan] Well, and I haven't been (sighs)
in Ridgecrest yet today,
but I don't blame them.
This has been goin' on for 48 hours now
and the shaking has been
very violent at times,
so people wanna be outside where they feel
at least a little bit safer.
And the problem is,
what we have learned is
that we can't predict earthquakes,
we can't predict when the
next one's going to happen.
We can try and give an advance warning,
but in that case, even
seconds is a good warning.
If there's a train
running through the area,
we can slow the train
down, maybe stop elevators,
but we don't have a
system that can predict,
from minutes away, when an
earthquake is going to happen.
- Bryan, thank you for taking the time.
I know you've probably
had little, if any, sleep,
so we appreciate your
calling in and updating us.
Bryan May with the Governor's
Office of Emergency Services.
Well, the President, by the
way, was briefed on all of this,
especially this morning with the updates
on that 7.1 magnitude earthquake.
Ellison Barber is right
now with the President
at Berkeley Heights,
where the Commander in Chief
is spending the weekend.
Ellison.
- Hey, Neil, yeah, the White House says
that President Trump was
briefed on the latest earthquake
in California overnight.
Around 1:00 a.m., the White House said
that they had teams closely
monitoring the situation
there in California
and said that they would
be providing updates
to the President throughout the night.
President Trump is in New
Jersey for the weekend,
staying at his golf club in Bedminster
and as of this morning,
Tweeting about immigration,
former Vice President Joe
Biden and the economy.
The Department of Labor
says the U.S. economy added
224,000 jobs in June,
that is up from 72,000 in May.
- Our country continues to do really well,
really, really well.
So we're very happy about it,
I think we're gonna be breaking records.
If we had a Fed that would
lower our interests rates,
we'd be like a rocket ship.
- President Trump
continued those critiques
of the Federal Reserve on
Twitter late last night,
writing, "Other countries
around the world are doing
"anything possible to take
advantage of the United States,
"knowing that our Federal
Reserve does not have a clue!"
He went on to Tweet that, "The
U.S.' most difficult problem
"is not our competitors,
but the Federal Reserve."
The President has come
under fire for his attacks
on the Federal Reserve and
the chairman, Jerome Powell,
for the last year.
The President has pretty
aggressively criticized
and repeatedly gone after
the Fed and the chairman.
He's criticized the Fed
for raising interest rates
and in the President's view,
not doing enough to help the U.S. economy.
Jay Powell has emphasized
that the Fed is independent
and earlier this year,
when asked about President
Trump's frequent criticisms,
Powell told reporters the Fed would
never take political
considerations into account
or discuss them as part of their work.
He said that their priority is working
for the American people.
Neil.
- Ellison, thank you very, very much.
Ellison Barber with the
President in New Jersey.
Meanwhile, with a strong
jobs report like that,
it is kinda tough to make the case
that the economy is just tanking.
So what do Democratic candidates
do in light of this report?
After this.
(wind howling)
♪ I want it that way ♪
- I can't believe it.
- That Carl brought his karaoke machine?
♪ Ain't nothin' but a heartache ♪
- No.
♪ Tell me why ♪
- I can't believe how easy
it was to save hundreds
of dollars on my car insurance with Geico.
♪ Tell me why ♪
♪ I never wanna hear you say ♪
- [Scientist] No, Kevin!
No, Kevin!
(wind howls)
No!
- No, no!
(door slams)
(scientist grunts)
♪ I want ♪
- [Announcer] Believe it,
Geico could save you 15%
or more on car insurance.
- Oh, my gosh! (laughs)
Wow!
Who am I? (laughs)
- Wow, is that really me? (laughs)
- [Jonathan] Hi, I'm Jonathan Greenhut,
the CEO of Plexaderm.
We've created the best offer yet
with our Plexaderm 10 minute challenge.
All it takes is 10 minutes
to reduce the appearance.
Of under-eye bags,
wrinkles and crow's feet.
Plexaderm works so well, makeup artists
and even people across the country look
and feel years younger in minutes.
- Hi, guys, my name is Sandy Marenesi,
I'm a professional hair and makeup artist
and one of the number one
question that I always get
in my chair is, "Can you
make me look younger?"
Now I could really say to people,
"Yes, I can make you look younger."
- My name is Robin and this
is what Plexaderm does for me.
- [Announcer] The instant results are
from naturally-based
silicates found in shell rock.
Once applied, your skin
tightens and firms.
Take action with the
Plexaderm 10 minute challenge.
Get up to 50% off the normal retail price,
plus get free shipping.
Visit plexaderm.com or call
the number on your screen.
- Every time I smiled,
I had to cover my mouth
because I was so ashamed.
When the denture slipped, I
would have to excuse myself
and go to the restroom,
virtually in tears.
It kept me from being
able to speak properly.
I could not eat corn,
apples, baby back ribs.
I did not want dentures
to be part of my life.
I pretty much decided dental
implants were the route
I was gonna take.
- Let's do a head-to-head comparison
of dental implants versus dentures.
With dentures, the ability to taste food,
to bite and chew is altered.
The worst thing about dentures, bone loss.
When you put an implant inside the bone,
which is like the root of a tooth,
now you've preserved the
bone, it's a game changer.
With implants, you walk into a restaurant,
you order anything you want.
You eat just like you have real teeth.
- Before you knew it, here I
was with my brand new teeth.
- [Announcer] Schedule your
free consultation today.
We'll even talk about financing options.
- I can smile, my confidence is back.
- [Announcer] Call Clear Choice today.
- My mom washes the dishes
before she puts them in the dishwasher.
So what does the dishwasher do?
- [Announcer] Cascade Platinum
does the work for you,
pre-washing and removing
stuck on foods the first time!
- Wow, that's clean!
- [Announcer] Cascade Platinum.
- When I book at hilton.com,
I get to select my room
from the floor plan,
free Wi-Fi and the price match guarantee!
- So with Hilton there is no catch.
- (laughs) Yeah, the only
catch is I'm never leaving.
(friend laughs)
No, I'm serious I live here now.
Book at hilton.com and get
the price match guarantee.
(dramatic music)
- And our economy is much
better than it's ever been.
From election day, we're over 50% increase
and we've made trillions
and trillions of dollars,
with a T, trillions.
- All right, that 50% increase
to which the President was referring
is the Dow Jones Industrial
surging about that
since he was first elected.
The President saying he's
a big reason for that
and optimism ahead of his inauguration
and what he's done since the inauguration
have made the changes
in a booming jobs report
that few people saw coming.
So for 2020 Democrats who
are portraying an economy
that isn't nearly as robust as
the numbers seem to indicate,
what do they do?
All In Together CEO
Lauren Leader is with us.
We got Republican strategist Joseph Pinion
and the host of "Sincerely
Kat" on Fox Nation, Kat Timpf.
Kat, end it with you, begin with you
on what the President is saying,
"No denying the numbers, give
me credit for those numbers."
- Right, I think that's the second part
that a lot of people have
a problem with, right.
The economy is doing very
well, that's objectively true
and this was a huge report in particular
because it shows that this
U.S.-China trade war hasn't
really affected employment
in this country negatively whatsoever.
But at the same time--
- Yet.
But they all say yet.
- Yet, yet.
As we always say on this show, though,
President Trump's approval
rating should be much better,
given how well the economy is doing.
So I think with any other
president it would be
and it has been.
We don't know how much
it's going to affect things
and then also at the same time,
polls haven't always
accurately represented just
how much support the President
has if you look back to 2016.
So it's really, really hard to say,
but it's gonna be hard for the Democrats
because they can't say that
the economy is a disaster,
it's hard to argue against
something that's doing so well.
- Lauren, you couldn't say
the economy is a disaster,
right, let's say?
- I just looked at this Gallup Poll
that was taken a couple
a couple of weeks ago
and compared it to a year ago,
which was independent of
asking political questions,
just asked Americans, "How
do you view the economy,
"great, good, poor?" et cetera.
46% of Americans still think
the economy is poor or very bad
and that's basically the same
number that it was a year ago.
And that tells you--
- How was it
under Barack Obama?
- Well, (sighs)
I didn't look at every single year.
I mean, I think, look, the confidence
and it was a different time, obviously,
because we were still
coming out of a recession,
out of the crisis, through
most of the Obama presidency.
The point is that I think Kat's right,
it should look like a
better picture than it feels
and I think the impact of the tariffs
on farmers in the Midwest,
I think the ongoing wage
growth is just now beginning
to change, it's starting to rise slightly.
But, you know, vast majorities
of Americans couldn't manage
a $200 unexpected medical
or emergency.
- But that's been the case
through Democrat and
Republican presidencies.
- Well, I know, but the point is
I think what the Democrats
are gonna do is make a lot
of hay out of that and say,
"Look, if the economy is so
good, why aren't we investing
"back in the working class Americans?
"Why are we not working
to reduce the debt?"
talk about the trillions with a T--
- Democrats like--
- I was gonna say--
- Well--
- Democrats lecturing on debt?
- What Democrats have been--
- Many have--
- Talking about the debt?
- Well, where is--
- That's like me giving dietary advice.
- It did--
- But having said that--
- Look at what they have--
- It's a valid point.
- To deal with!
- All right, but--
- The debt has exploded
under this administration.
- Well, it exploded--
- I think they're gonna take
it on.
- Under the prior one.
So any party lecturing the other on debt
I think is a fool's game,
but, Joseph, one of
the things I do note is
that the President hasn't really been able
to take advantage of
this, at least in polling
to some of the points that were raised,
is that there are one million
more African-Americans employed
than when Barack Obama left office,
more than two million Hispanics
than when Barack Obama left office.
Yet with those groups,
he's still under water,
why is that?
- I think that realistically,
they've just done a bad job
of messaging across the board.
I think they're actually
better served not makin'
it about African-American
employment or Hispanic employment,
but just sayin' that,
"Look, we've got a problem
"with poverty in this country,
"but that problem pre-existed
my administration.
"Having said that, if
Democrats are tellin' ya
"that people are working
two and three jobs,
"they've been working two or three jobs
"this whole time.
"The difference is, those two
"and three jobs are paying more money
"under my administration."
- All right, well--
- But, well--
- It's one in 15 who are
working two or more jobs.
That's a high number nevertheless,
but it is in this idea that
everybody's working that.
But I--
- And wage growth,
the wage growth is ticking up
as the job growth is ticking up.
Wage growth for African-Americans
and Hispanics has not kept pace--
- Well, for lower--
- With the wage growth
for the white Americans.
- And middle income workers
you're actually wrong on that.
It's been running at
close to a 3.3 to 3 1/2%--
- [Lauren] And it's double that
though for white Americans.
- Well, no, no--
- It is!
- I mean.
- I just looked at the numbers--
- Before I walked on.
- The fact of the matter is,
I mean, for upper income,
which tends to be a target
of Democrats, it's been
averaging closer to 3%.
No, that's not narrowing the
gap, but it is beginning to.
So what I'm looking at with this is
whether the arguments
that Democrats are raising
on the stump camp is gonna
come back to bite them
because most people look
at this recovery would say,
"I can deal with this."
- Right, absolutely and I
think it's gonna be tough.
I think that's why we've seen them focus
on other things such as healthcare,
that's a good thing, I
think, for them to focus on
because obviously Republicans
had a chance to fix that
and that got all messed up.
That's didn't happen,
they didn't have an answer--
- How much of a role does--
- to the problem.
- The President
himself play in this?
I think he stomps on his own--
- I absolutely--
- otherwise good message?
- I absolutely think--
- Tweeting silly stuff,
and he gets away.
- He distracts from the message
of the economy doing so well.
Yes, he talks about it but
then he'll Tweet something
that's all the way out there
or he'll go after somebody,
call someone a loser
and people tend to focus on those things
more than--
- Oh, I can see the Tweets--
- They focus on the economy.
- Coming on you right now.
- I'm a loser, I already know I'm a loser,
so what are ya gonna do?
(Neil laughs)
- All right, one other
thing, Lauren, I look at
when I look at all the data that comes in
and you're right, we get a lot
of it from a lot of angles,
is that in the manufacturing states,
some of the big ones like
Pennsylvania, Michigan, Indiana,
we are talking about wages growing
at a faster clip than
the rest of the nation.
Yet, to your point, he is
trailing, that is the President,
by double digits in some of these,
not quite that same amount in Indiana,
but that doesn't jive with these numbers.
- Well, because you have to
look at the whole picture.
Look, at the same time that we've had
this sort of incremental growth in wages,
which I don't deny, it's real
and obviously the growth in jobs,
you also have this
explosion of student debt.
So the access to the American
dream has gotten more
and more expensive, it's
weighing down more families,
not just the kids who are going to school,
but their parents and their grandparents
who are saddled with debt.
You look at the rising cost of healthcare,
the rising cost of housing,
which the Democrats have
just started talking about.
The cost of living in almost
every metropolitan area
around the--
- Would the government waving
a wand to eradicate that debt,
or to deal with Health Care For All,
or to offer benefits to illegals--
- Look, I--
- Do you think
that is enough to turn the tide for now
or do other Americans
look at that and say,
"Whoa, whoa, whoa, cool it."
- Look, I think that the
risk the President runs is
this sense that he's tone deaf
to the challenges that working-class
and middle-class Americans
are actually facing.
He keeps talkin' about how
amazing the stock market is,
well, the vast majority
of working-class folks aren't invested
or benefiting from the stock market,
except maybe for a 401k and those--
- Well, 54% are you're right--
- Okay, so then--
there's another 46%--
- It's down from 60%.
- I mean, we could do the math.
The point is, is that
you continue to only--
- But what about all these numbers
I showed you on minority gains
all of that?
- You have to,
all of the polls that ask Americans,
or working-class Americans, how they feel,
do they feel the sense
that they are benefiting
from this economy, the
answer is no they do not--
- So when the give--
- Because of the--
whole picture.
- The President high marks
on the economy, but overall,
not for him, himself,
what does that tell you, Joseph?
- Right, and the Democrats
have an opportunity there
to say, "And I have a solution for that."
But, I mean, that's--
- But it hasn't changed--
- Part of why--
- The view
that the economy's doing well.
- I think the reality is that
the overwhelming majority
of Americans do feel that
the economy is going well.
I think that if you look,
again, not everyone is
invested in the stock market,
but it's gonna be very
difficult for Democrats to say--
- By the way, that masks
the number who benefit
from a higher market, or who see things
in their pension funds that are directly,
or indirectly invested.
- Yeah, market confidence
is very much an indicator
on how the actual commercial impact
and so I think if you
just take a step back
and say the realistic--
- But that's dangerous, right?
- [Lauren] It's huge, yes.
- Constantly quoting the stock market.
Ronald Reagan, of all people
for whom the market boomed,
was very leery.
- It's extremely dangerous.
- Look, I recognize the fact that, again,
there are going to be people who says,
"I am not included in this growth,"
but I think it's going to
be difficult for Democrats
to stand up there and say,
"Your 401k goin' up is a
figment of your imagination."
The extra money--
- But maybe her point--
- You got back--
- About those
who will capitalize on the fact--
- It's a small piece of it.
- That they don't,
maybe on these wedge issues
and what you're doing
on illegal immigrants
and Health Care For All, will
register, what do you think?
- Well, I--
- No, I'm saying
it's a bigger picture than
just the stock market.
What their day-to-day lives are--
- But you mention these examples
as something that will eek out support
where there isn't,
maybe on the general economy.
- Yeah, and look,
the Democrats are gonna have a big stage
for the next six months,
to be dominating endless conversations
about policy solutions for
making American's lives better.
They're gonna own that
and the President is gonna
eventually have to address--
- But they're at a step--
- What is he gonna do with--
- With even Democratic voters
who don't support giving
health benefits to illegals.
- I just think in a binary--
- It's not presented--
- Choice between somebody who
didn't have a job yesterday
and somebody who has a job tomorrow,
they're not going to be
able to convince them
that somehow their life is worse off.
I think that people, again,
in polls early on are gonna
be talkin' about the emotions,
the visceral impact that
Donald Trump's words has
on their everyday life.
But I think when you show up in November,
when you start doing that polling,
the actual only polling that matter,
which is the exit polling,
I think there's gonna
be much different story.
- So we're just wasting our time
with the polls.
(Joseph laughs)
- What are we gonna do--
- I don't know?
- For the next year?
- I don't know.
Guys, I'm gonna see ya soon again here.
The President, he mentioned something,
"We've never seen this
kind of strength before,"
then why, Mr. President, are
you urging the Federal Reserve
to cut interest rates?
You don't need to if we're
firing on all the cylinders.
Or is there something I'm missing?
Apparently there is, right after this.
(bird squawking)
(shoes tapping)
(phone dings)
(crowd cheers)
- Hey, who are you?
- Oh, hey, Jeb, I'm a car thief.
- What!
- I'm here to steal your car
because, well, that's my job.
- What!
- What?
- (laughs) What!
- What!
- What?
(glass shattering)
- What!
- (laughs) It happens.
Have you got cut-rate car insurance?
Payin' for this could feel
like gettin' robbed twice.
So get Allstate.
(engine revs)
(tires squeal)
And be better protected
from mayhem.
(metal crashes)
(tires squeal)
Like me. (laughs)
(sinister music)
- What if there was something
that can reduce body fat,
boost mood, get rid of
wrinkles, tighten saggy skin
and make you look and
feel decades, not years,
but decades younger?
I'm talking about human
growth hormone, or HGH.
Finally, there's SeroVital.
- [Announcer] In a clinical trial,
SeroVital has been shown to
boost your HGH naturally,
up to an astonishing 682%.
- SeroVital gave me my youth back.
- [Announcer] SeroVital, available at ULTA
and smarter retailers nationwide.
- [Announcer] Their quest
for a record fourth World
Cup comes down to the final.
- [Commentator] Header!
Goal!
(crowd cheers)
- [Announcer] It's now all or nothing
for the Stars and Stripes
as Megan Rapinoe and
Alex Morgan lead the U.S.
- Unstoppable!
- Against the Netherlands.
- [Commentator] Spectacular!
- [Announcer] The reigning champs put
their legacy on the line.
- [Commentator] Goal!
- [Announcer] One
last time!
The World Cup final,
coverage begins tomorrow
at 10:00 a.m. Eastern on
FOX and the FOX Sports App.
- [Announcer] This is the
couple who wanted to get away,
who used Expedia to
book the vacation rental
which led to the discovery
that sometimes a little
downtime can lift you right up.
Expedia, everything you need to go.
(app beeps)
(engine hums)
- [Announcer] From two stories to 20,
from ready apps to emergency response,
whenever damage strikes,
call on the cleanup team that's
fast to any size disaster
at 1-800-SERVPRO.
Like it never even happened.
- Our nation is stronger today
than it ever was before.
- [Announcer] Inside the President's
July Fourth Celebration.
Judge Jeanine breaks it
down like no one else,
only on "Justice".
(bat clinks)
(crowd cheers)
- Coach, it's kinda hard to see the ball.
- I've been there.
I had a TV service with
hardly any sports in 4K,
couldn't see any of the quality details.
I switched to DirecTV,
now I get the most live sports in 4K.
- So, how does that help me?
- It really doesn't, I don't
know why I told ya that?
Go get 'em, sport!
- [Announcer] Live sports
that aren't in 4K are just kinda TV.
Don't just kinda TV, DirecTV.
Don't have 4K?
Call 1-855-WATCH-4K and ask for it today.
- [Announcer] This
summer, all eyes will be
on the U.S. Women's National Team
in the FIFA Women's World Cup.
♪ Did you hear ♪
(crowd cheers)
♪ There's a battle to fight ♪
- [Announcer] Over 153 hours of coverage.
Live from France, the 2019
FIFA Women's World Cup
on FOX FS1 and FS2.
Don't miss all 52 matches of
the FIFA Women's World Cup,
live in stunning 4K on DirecTV.
If you don't have 4K, ask for it today.
(dramatic music)
- All right, getting our first
images from California now.
Shake, rattle and rolled,
they're getting earthquake-related images
from around Ridgecrest, California
as the sun begins to rise there.
This coming in, these images from KTTV.
As you might have heard,
a 7.1 magnitude earthquake in the region,
higher by a factor 10 times than the one
that hit just 24 hours earlier.
We're watching this, no
reports of any serious injuries
or worse so far, so there is that.
We'll keep ya posted on aftershocks
and obviously a lot of
Californians worried
that they could see a lot more of those.
In the meantime, the job market
is stronger than all get out
right now, in fact so strong,
it has a lot of folks saying,
"Do we really even need
"to see the Federal
Reserve cut interests rates
"to keep it going?"
And that lands the
conundrum for stock traders
because they sold off
a little bit yesterday
from record highs, we reached
before July 4th, the holiday,
on the notion that maybe there is no need
to at least immediately cut rates.
Let's get the view from
Gibbs Wealth Management,
Chief Investment Officer, Erin Gibbs,
we've got FOX News
Contributor Jonas Max Ferris
and our very own FOX Business
Network Deirdre Bolton.
Deirdre, that was sort of the battle back
and forth yesterday, wasn't it?
Well, you know, it's
strong and we like that,
good news is good news, but it's bad news
when it means the Federal
Reserve might have to push off--
- Yeah and if we look at--
- A rate cut.
- Fed funds futures, so what
traders are anticipating,
so it seems as if
everyone, or most people,
are still anticipating this cut in July,
but the idea of a 50 basis
point cut seems to be--
- That's off the table now--
- Really diminishing.
Yeah, it's seems to be not
even really a real possibility,
but the 25 basis point is a possibility.
But to your point, do we need at all
and if so, do we need it now,
those are the two outstanding questions.
So the market clearly pricing it in,
as far as what's coming,
I'm gonna bet on the 25 basis point cut--
- So we'll still see a cut?
- I believe so.
- [Neil] You think that,
we're gonna still see a cut?
- Yeah, because of really
the last big piece of data
that the Fed was getting was last Friday
and because there were a
few things that you weren't
completely thrilled with--
- Like what?
- Well, for one, some of the
wage growth started to drop
and even though they--
- Was it 3.1%?
- Yeah, so just not quite as strong,
so I think those kind of indicators.
There's still a concern
about trade war out there,
I mean, we haven't gotten rid of it,
we're just slowly moving forward.
And also Europe, still,
the last time they talked,
the big issue was concerns
about a global economic slowdown
and we still have that out there,
so though the U.S. is good.
So I think a quarter point is
still very much on the table
for the end of July.
- You know, I always
wondered, Jonas, on this
whether you go ahead and cut rates now,
and in our environment,
we have a strong economy,
albeit maybe not as strong as we had,
but you don't have a lot
of arrows in the quiver
so do you waste your time
cutting 'em an environment
as good as this when you might
really need 'em down the road?
- Yeah, it's like in that movie,
"The Fast and the Furious"
when he hit the nitrous too early
and he's like, "You ran outta nitrous!"
The reality--
- I thought the exact same thing!
(group laughs)
Touche.
- I think that's psychological
"Wizard of Oz" kind of thing
that the Fed does, it's
very important in this.
On just pure inflation terms,
they could have lower interest rates,
it would be good to have
the interest rate curve be
upward-slanting, so
people aren't concerned
we're gonna have a recession.
That said, if they do that
now and go to 1% or 1.5,
and then we do get a recession--
- [Neil] What are we now,
around 2.5, is that it?
- Yeah, a little under
with the actual, anyway.
(Neil huffs)
- Yes.
- If they do that,
then people are gonna be like,
wait a second, we're already
recycling the QE money,
we stopped doing that.
We're already now down to 1%.
We've already done tax cuts,
we're not gonna get those again.
We're already running a stimulus program,
essentially increase spending.
What are we gonna do now, a little panic,
and the Fed wants to show off
that they've got some tools.
They really don't have that
many tools left at this point,
so they don't wanna--
- It's quantitative easing
and buying all the Treasury
notes and bonds out there.
That was kind of unprecedented
when Bernanke was doing that, right.
- Right, and they can't get out of it.
I mean, they're trying
to slowly, so slowly,
let's let the interest payments be
basically burned, that money.
Instead they have to now
go buy more longterm debt,
which is one of the reasons
longer term interest rates fell
so much, besides these fears
that are kinda irrational,
that the economy's slowing,
which kinda gets to the whole thing,
What's going on is, you know,
the market long term is
earnings, economy, all that,
but in the short run, there
was a big bet going on
that the economy's weakening
enough to get the Fed
to lower rates, but
actually is not that weak,
so we're gonna get a big
boost in the stock market.
That's what investors were hoping for
and that story changed when
this jobs numbers stood.
- Well, when they say
you can't lose, that a good
report will be greeted favorably
as a good report, a bad report
would be greeted favorably
as a reason for the Fed
to ease, that sets you up
for a disappointment.
- That's the idea
where you were saying that
good news is bad news,
bad news is good news.
But I'm seeing more and more, I mean,
when you talk about the tools,
I think the Fed has also decided
that by cutting rates
or not cutting rates,
that everyone understands in the market,
whereas the QE was very difficult
and there was a bit of hocus pocus.
I mean, I'm sure there was a method--
- Well, the President--
- To the madness.
- Was a critic of it.
- Yes.
- What was goin' on under Barack Obama--
- But to me--
- Now he says,
"Do that for me"--
- Right, do that.
- "And we'd be really off to the races."
- Put that special sauce
back in there, please.
- Do think so, that that's the case?
- Yeah, it's definitely something
that could be added back in.
But it's--
- [Neil] Do you think
we should add it back?
- No, I think the tightening has been,
because they just let it get
so out of hand for so long
and I think just small
quarter-point rate cuts.
I think the idea of when we
were thinking about a 50-bip cut
for the July meeting
was a little aggressive.
So I think the expectations now seem--
- Yeah, and you more--
- Much more rational.
- And more general press talking even
about deflationary worries, right.
To your point, there were
a lot of people saying,
okay, maybe we don't need this now,
but there were definite
arguments being made
in Washington Post,
editorials in The Journal,
The Economist, Bloomberg Business Week,
you know, nobody's
saying this is happening,
but saying, okay, should this be,
actually now what we're worried about?
- I just wonder--
- And you could slow down--
- The trade thing, though.
The trade thing holds everything in it.
I always think we haven't
gotten the impact of tariffs yet
because a lot of them haven't
reached consumers yet,
because they were in transit and all that.
So obviously, eventually that will happen,
we don't know when, but
if they get a trade deal,
all bets are off, right?
- You know the funny thing is
that we do lower interest rates,
or they keep going down,
our weakening dollar would have the effect
of more than the tariff, actually.
So it would make all imports
from all countries seem more
than five, or 10, or 15% expense.
In fact, I believe the
President was talking about
that by having rates too
high, our dollar's too strong.
So he wants to--
- So you cut them.
Weaken them, obviously it would improve--
It would improve--
- Right, 'cause--
- Exporters getting--
- Other countries--
- Their goods out--
- Yeah, people
in Germany are very happy
with our 2% 10-year bond
because they have a zero or
negative 10-year bond, so--
- Yeah, in Germany, you're actually paying
for the privilege to lend
your money to the government.
I mean, they have negative rates.
- That's incredible, are we going there?
- I don't see us going
anywhere near negative rates.
We're in a much healthier
environment versus Europe.
They're really struggling--
- So are you bullish--
- Just to get any growth.
- At this stage?
- Yeah, I think--
- We are?
- Yeah, we are, I'm bullish.
But I'm cautious, let's say I'm--
- Cautiously bullish.
- Cautiously optimistic.
- [Neil] Jonas?
- We would probably be
at about 1% if we did
and there's two reasons.
We have a stronger economy
with stronger inflation
than Europe, but we also borrow much more.
We're in a huge, actual budget deficits
that they don't run anymore.
They're running a very
strict, austere program,
they're not borrowing as much as we are.
- Yeah, it can boomerang on you.
All right, guys, I know you'll be back.
In the meantime, the battle
between New York Democratic Congresswoman,
Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez
and the border patrol,
erupting over new allegations
that this Facebook postings,
that were pretty obnoxious,
there might have been more
of them than we thought
and more involved in
saying what they said.
After this.
- With all that USAA offers,
why go with anybody else?
We know their rates are good.
We know that they're always
gonna take care of us.
- It was an instant savings
and I should have changed a long time ago.
- We're the Tenneys and
we're USAA members for life.
- [Announcer] Call USAA to
start saving on insurance today.
- I'm really into this car,
but how do I know if
I'm getting a good deal?
I tell TrueCar my zip and which car I want
and TrueCar shows the
range of prices people
in my area actually paid for the same car,
so I know if I'm getting a great price.
This is how car buying
was always meant to be.
This is TrueCar.
(dramatic music)
(lighter clicking)
(egg tapping)
(food sizzling)
(rooster crows)
(metal scrapes)
(bacon sizzles)
(dramatic guitar music)
(metal scrapes)
(bottle top clinks)
(food sizzles)
- [Announcer] Introducing
the Blackstone griddle.
Outdoor cooking without the compromise.
Log on now to blackstoneproducts.com.
(bird screeching)
- [Announcer] Beat by the heat?
Are you tired of those
hot, sticky, sweaty days?
No matter what you do,
you can't get relief
from the sun's scorching rays!
Now, there's the Arctic hat,
the evaporative-cooling hat
that keeps you 20 degrees cooler
than the outside temperature!
And has a built-in UV barrier
that reflects the sun's heat
and harmful UV rays.
Just put it on for instant
relief from the sun,
or wet the inner liner and get
the ultimate cooling relief.
You'll feel 20 degrees cooler instantly
and it will keep you cool for hours!
The secret is hydro-chill technology,
an evaporative lining holds
and gradually releases water
for continuous cooling,
while the built-in UV
barrier blocks over 99%
of the sun's harmful rays,
keeping you cool and
comfortable all day long.
Look, this man's head is
a scorching 102 degrees,
but with Arctic Hat,
he's a comfortable 78.
That's over 20 degrees cooler!
Breathable and light-weight
with ventilated panels
that allow air to flow freely.
It's perfect for the
beach or going for a hike,
all kinds of outdoor activities!
It's like having a
personal air conditioner
everywhere you go!
Whether you're out enjoying
nature or working in the yard,
the Arctic Hat will be
your cooling companion.
- I'm always outside working in the heat,
but with the Arctic Hat,
I'm feelin' cool and comfortable all day.
- I burn very easily,
but the Arctic Hat's UV
protection let's me stay outside
a lot longer without worry.
- [Announcer] It's fully
adjustable so one size fits all!
So get outside and stay cool
and protected with Arctic Hat!
Call now and get the Arctic Hat
in your choice of brimmed
hat or cap for just $19.99!
Plus, every order today
gets free shipping!
But order right now and
we'll double the offer,
just pay a separate fee.
You get two Arctic Hats and free shipping
for only $19.99!
Order now!
- [Announcer] To order,
call 1-800-417-0992
or go online at buyarctichat.com.
Don't delay, call 1-800-417-0992
Order now.
- [Announcer] Who!
- I like to plan my activities
before I take a trip
so by the time I get there,
I can just enjoy the ride!
With TripAdvisor, it's easy to discover
over 100,000 bookable things to do!
From walking tours in Rome,
to wine tastings in Tuscany
and if you like what you see,
you can book it with ease!
Just another way
TripAdvisor helps you make
your trip a masterpiece!
- Who!
- [Owl] Read reviews, check
hotel prices, book things to do.
TripAdvisor.
(dramatic music)
- All right, President Trump
just Tweeted this morning
that, "Democrats must change
the loophole in asylum laws
"but they probably won't.
"They want open borders,
"which means massive crime and drugs!"
This as the border patrol
is telling FOX News
that it is looking into these
recent allegations of agents,
former agents, making
controversial comments and more
about lawmakers and illegal
immigrants themselves
in a second private Facebook group,
and one that was taken down
later than the first one.
Anyway, it's a bit confusing.
Let's get the read
from the National Border
Patrol Council President,
back with us, Brandon Judd.
Brandon, good to have you.
- Thank you, I appreciate
bein' on with you.
- Do you know, Brandon,
the latest wave of these Facebook postings
that apparently involve more
agents, and former agents,
than the original roundup
that was critical of illegals
who are being held at
these detention centers,
and even those visiting detention centers?
- I do, there's a couple Facebook
pages that are out there.
You've got the "I'm 10-15",
you've got the "I'm 10-15x2",
you've got "The Real CBP Nation".
All of these Facebook
pages have been critical
of illegal aliens,
they've been critical
of certain lawmakers.
Now there's some things
that have been posted
on those Facebook pages
that are perfectly fine,
they're political talk and
you can actually do that.
But there's other things that
are absolutely reprehensible
and I'm aware that there's
been about 13 letters
that have been sent out
to current employees
that are cease and desist letters,
telling them that they need
to stop their Facebook posts
and that's just the initial.
Now the investigation has to go into,
were these posts of the
nature that violates policy?
And if they were, those individuals
will be held accountable
and they need to be held accountable.
- When you say, "held accountable," fired?
- It could be, it strictly depends
on what the nature of the posts were.
I mean, if they're bad enough,
if they're releasing information
about law enforcement,
sensitive information,
they're gonna be very,
very strict sanctions--
- What if they were--
- And yes, they could be.
- Just disparaging,
or sometimes deemed, racist, comments?
Would you--
- Oh, there--
- Would you fire them for that?
- Yes, if they're racist
comments, absolutely.
We cannot, as uniformed law enforcement,
we cannot show that we have a bias.
If we have a bias,
then you cannot properly enforce the laws.
There is no place in law enforcement
for individuals that are racist.
There's no place in law enforcement
for people that hate
other groups of people
because you obviously cannot
enforce the laws properly
if you're already bringing
that bias into the workplace.
- You know, Brandon,
the reason why I asked that
is Senator Chuck Schumer had
called for the firing of
Mark Morgan on all this,
the acting commissioner
of the Customs and Border Protection--
- That's wrong.
- Ultimately picked to lead the agency
because of what was happening
under him, what do you think?
- No, that's absolutely wrong.
In fact, Commissioner
Morgan, I can tell ya
that when he was the chief
of the Border Patrol,
he was made aware of just one post
and he immediately took action
and he took the most severe action
that he possibly could have taken
under labor laws at that time.
So Commissioner Morgan,
currently Commissioner Morgan,
he did what he needed to do.
What's funny is Senator Schumer
called for his termination
before he was even the commissioner.
I mean, he's over at ICE,
he was the director of ICE
and Senator Schumer is
calling for his termination
when he's not even the commissioner.
Senator Schumer has it
completely and totally wrong.
He needs to look deeper and
he needs to look at the people
that have been here for an awful-long time
that should have been aware of this
and should have been taking proper action.
- You know, I don't know
where the truth starts
or the exaggerations begin
on these Facebook postings,
but one of the things that Politico
and others have reported, Brandon,
is that higher ups were aware of this,
they weren't proud of
it, but they were aware.
Do you know anything about any of this?
- They absolutely were aware of this.
CBP is required to monitor
what agents are doing,
whether it's on duty, off duty.
These Facebook pages, they
were aware of these pages,
I mean, you had a great--
- And did they tell them
to take them down?
Or did they take it down?
- No, no they didn't.
In fact, if you look at
these Facebook pages,
there were a great many
high-level managers
that were on these pages.
So yes, they were absolutely aware of it,
they did have a responsibility
to do something about it
and they didn't.
Again, I'm gonna point back to 2017,
almost two years to the date,
the National Border Patrol
Council sent out an advisory
to agents telling them,
"You need to be careful
"about what you're posting on Facebook.
"There are certain
things that you can post,
"but there are certain things
"that are absolutely inappropriate
"and could potentially
affect your job status."
And CBP didn't follow up.
I mean, if you look at the Facebook posts,
the National Border Patrol Council,
we were the first ones to come
out and condemn those posts
when the ProPublica article broke.
The agency came in later after us
and this is what happens
on a very regular basis
and frankly, it's very frustrating to us.
We want the most honorable
organization that we can have.
This agency is a very important agency,
the work that we do is extremely important
for the American public.
We are charged with securing the border
and we have to do it properly
and have to have the
right agents to do it.
- Brandon, we'll watch closely,
thank you for taking the time.
Brandon Judd, the National
Border Patrol Council President,
joining us out of Salt Lake City.
Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
- Meanwhile, I want to show you
what's happening in California right now.
This is Ridgecrest.
Thankfully, no reports
of significant injuries,
but as you can see, there
were structure fires
as a result of gas leaks
throughout the city.
The state's emergency services
director leaving the door
open for the possibility that
still more serious damage
as daylight emerges and they're
able to reassess all of this
in the wake of a 7.1 magnitude
follow up earthquake,
after a 6.4 magnitude
earthquake just the day before.
That is technically 10 times more serious.
More after this.
- [Announcer] The ant
mindlessly marches on,
carrying up to 50 times its body weight.
It never questions the task at hand.
(engine roars)
But this year, there's a more
thrilling path to follow.
(engine roars)
- Kids!
(metal creaks)
Change of plans!
(kids laugh)
- [Announcer] Defy the
laws of human nature
at the Summer of Audi Sales Event.
Get exceptional offers now.
(dramatic music)
(heart beating)
- I heard ya the first time,
I just wanted to hear it again.
- [Announcer] Now
available at walmart.com.
World-class rechargeable
hearing aid for hundreds,
not thousands of dollars.
Including our new
app-controlled hearing aid
that gives you full control
of your sound environment.
Try them in the comfort
of your home for 60 days!
Our full lineup available
with free two-day shipping,
now at walmart.com.
- Hearing Assist will change your life!
- Hi, I'm Alex Schulze!
- And I'm Andrew Cooper!
- In 2015, we took a surf
trip to Bali, Indonesia
and saw first-hand,
just how bad the world's plastic
pollution crisis really is.
We wanted to make it our
mission to solve this problem
and we have.
- [Andrew] We started cleaning the ocean
by ourselves until 2017,
when we started our ocean
cleanup company, 4ocean.
- Now, we've become the world's largest
ocean cleanup company,
employing captains and
crews seven days a week
to clean our oceans and coastlines.
We've operated out of
27 different countries
and to date, we've removed
over two million pounds
of trash from the ocean.
And now, we're inviting you
to join the clean ocean movement.
- [Andrew] All of our
cleanup efforts are funded
entirely through the sale of our bracelet.
The 4ocean bracelet is
made from our ocean plastic
and the recycled glass
bottles that we collect.
- Every bracelet purchased
helps fund the removal
of one pound of trash from the ocean
and supports the 4ocean cleanup movement.
- So visit 4ocean.com today to
become part of the solution.
(upbeat music)
- All right, I'm getting in the car now,
I'll see ya soon.
- Okay, sounds like a plan!
Whoa!
(mysterious music)
Lisa?
- Sorry, I dropped ya.
- It's really dark down here.
Oh, there's some change down here, too.
- [Announcer] Don't
let this happen to you.
With removable cups, the
WeatherTech CupFone fits
virtually any size cup holder
and it adjusts to secure
virtually any size phone.
Tilts for perfect viewing
and even allows easy
access while charging.
- That's better!
- [Announcer] Order your
American-made CupFone today
at weathertech.com.
- [Announcer] Hey, renovators,
time to dream bigger!
(sultry music)
♪ Wayfair, you're my new secret weapon ♪
♪ You got what I need for my renovation ♪
♪ I love all these options ♪
♪ So much to choose from ♪
♪ Bathrooms and basements,
even my kitchen ♪
♪ Your service is sweet ♪
♪ And my job is complete ♪
♪ Wayfair, here I come ♪
- [Announcer] Start your
renovation at wayfair.com.
(dramatic music)
- All right, we try to be
very fair and balanced here.
We just heard from the border
patrol unity, Brandon Judd,
now to a border state
Democrat who isn't impressed
with what he's been hearing
out of border officials.
Texas Democratic Congressman Al Green.
Congressman, very good to have you.
- Good to be with you, Mr. Cavuto.
- Neil, please, you're the
congressman, the big cheese here,
not me.
- (laughs) You're kind.
You're kind.
- So let me get your take
on what Brandon Judd was just saying, sir,
that if he finds that
people have made, in fact,
these obnoxious comments,
border agents have been
charged with making
on these Facebook posts, since taken down,
he would advocate firing them.
Is that good enough for you?
- Yes, it is good enough.
I'm sure there are other things
that can be done, as well,
but if a person exhibits racial views
that are abhorrent, racism as
it was called by the agent,
by the way, I commend him, I
think that it is appropriate
to consider terminating the relationship.
- This measure that was
overwhelmingly approved
in Congress, the $4.6 billion funding
to deal with the crisis at the border,
did you vote for that?
- I did.
- And you did so to ease the congestion
and the problems with the
kids and everyone else, right?
- Well, I did so for a
multiplicity of reasons
and I understand why
those who did not do so.
I did so because, quite frankly,
I've been talkin' for some time
about the conditions at the border.
I went there, I saw the conditions
and I wanted to do what
I could, in my own way,
to be helpful.
But I understand that
those who chose not too,
to, in a sense, highlight the fact
that there needs to be more transparency,
there needs to be more accountability.
I respect what they did.
For me, seeing that baby with her father
on the shores of the river,
that touched my heart in a way
such that it was impossible
for me to vote otherwise.
- You know, as you've
pointed out, Congressman,
these children popping up
in these migrant centers
is quintuple what it was
under Barack Obama, under whom
these facilities were built
in the first place, but
not prepared for the crowds
that fill these facilities today.
So is this really the agent's fault,
or for that matter even Homeland Security?
- Mr. Cavuto, I thank you
for asking the question
because it's a question that
really merits an answer.
The question is this,
are we there to facilitate
the law, or are we there
to deter people from
coming into the country?
In the early part of the 19th century,
we were processing five
to 10,000 people per day.
We never separated children
from their parents.
Persons were fleeing
Scandinavia and Eastern Europe
and they came by the millions
and we processed them.
The question is, do we really
want to process people,
if we do, we can,
or do we want to find the means
by which we can deter them
from coming?
- But you would have
to admit to the--
- I believe--
- You would have to admit that
these numbers are staggering,
even dwarfing what Barack
Obama was dealing with
when he, too, would look
into briefly separating kids
from families just to make
sure that those with whom
they were traveling were in
fact, that they're related.
- Well, compared to those
who were comin' through Ellis Island,
they are not dwarfing
numbers, especially given--
- But this isn't Ellis Island.
- They didn't have--
- This is right at our border.
- The computer equipment
that we have currently.
- This is a very different case,
right here, right there, right now.
So do you think--
- Well, Ellis Island--
- That the $4.6 billion
that's been allocated
to deal with this, would you be happy
if it's still the same
folks in charge of this,
or do you want someone else running it?
- Well, let me continue,
I have to say this
and I'll answer your question.
But those who were coming
through Ellis Island were right
there, right then and we respected them
and we welcomed them.
There seems to be a removal
of the welcome mat for those
who are coming from--
- No, no, no, no--
- South of the border.
- We welcomed them
because they had assurances
that there were family or
friends who take them in,
who could take care of them
and not the United States government,
very different environment.
- Well, a good many of
them did not, Mr. Cavuto,
and by the way, a good many of the people
who were coming from south of the border,
they have family, friends
and persons who can assist them, as well,
but we are turning them away
without even giving them an interview
to a certain extent now,
by pushing the interview
process to Mexico.
And now, to your question about
whether or not the persons who
are in charge are the persons
who should remain in charge,
it's my opinion that
persons who are in charge,
some of them are victims themselves
because they are forced
to enforce policies
that, quite frankly, are abhorrent.
A policy of separating
children from their parents,
no country should have such a policy
and we should--
- Well, you can understand--
- Not be proud of this.
- Why it happens, though.
I mean, in the cases where--
- No, I cannot.
- All right, so--
- I cannot.
- When Barack Obama was entertaining that
because he simply didn't know where a lot
of these kids were coming from,
now he didn't formally separate them
for extended periods of time,
but he recognized that some
of them were being used
as leverage to get into this country.
- Among any group of folk,
you'll have some things
that are not appropriate,
but the overwhelming majority
of these people are coming here
to escape persecution,
escape crime.
I just returned from El Salvador.
I went there to bring back a constituent
who had been deported
and we brought him home.
He had a 10-year bar
on him, a Mr. Escobar,
he was married to an American woman,
he had two American-born children,
he reported to ICE and he was deported
with the money in his pocket
and the clothes on his back.
We brought him home.
So I think it's the attitude
that we have to deal with, Mr. Cavuto.
I really do and listen,
let me thank you for giving
me the opportunity to say that
because quite frankly, we are finding
that it's difficult to
get that message out
and I appreciate it.
- Well, no, I appreciate
you're coming on, Congressman.
That commercial, unfortunately,
won't stop for love or money
but I want to thank you.
Al Green of Texas.
- Thank you, sir.
Much more after this.
(romantic piano music)
(record screeches)
(upbeat club music)
♪ Can I put in a request ♪
(crowd exclaiming)
♪ Don't have no sense about this ♪
(crowd cheering)
♪ Can't take no cuss about this ♪
♪ Like this ♪
- [Announcer] This is a
moment you planned for.
To start your investment plan,
find an advisor at massmutual.com.
(light piano music)
- When my doctor put me
on a cholesterol-lowering statin drug,
I knew I should take CoQ10 with it.
I take Qunol CoQ10.
(water splashes)
Why?
Because Qunol has three
times better absorption
than regular CoQ10.
Qunol, the better CoQ10.
- No matter what I wore,
I worried someone might see
my bladder-leak underwear,
so I switched to Always Discreet Boutique.
It's shape-hugging threads
smooth out the back,
so it fits better than
Depend and no one notices.
(light music)
Always Discreet.
- [Announcer] Campaign 2020,
from the President's
Fourth of July Celebration,
to Democrats pushing their positions,
inside every move and message to win votes
on "FOX News Sunday".
- I just couldn't stay
in shape like I used to,
but luckily, I found Nugenix.
- [Announcer] Nugenix has a
unique man-boosting formula
that helps increase your
free testosterone level.
To get a complementary bottle,
text BEST to 42424.
(lively horn music)
- [Announcer] Want a $10 Amazon gift card?
(tyrannosaurus roars)
Sign up forCuriosityStream today
and get a $10 Amazon gift car on us.
You'll get access to thousands
of non-fiction titles.
- [Neil] That's affirmative.
- [Announcer] We've got
somethin' for everyone.
- You don't have to look
any further than this.
- [Announcer] $19.99 gets you
one year of CuriosityStream.
- That really ignites the imagination.
- [Announcer] And a $10 Amazon gift card.
Sign up now.
(dramatic music)
- [Announcer] Get a free mesothelioma book
from mesobook.com.
- People who have been diagnosed
with mesothelioma have many questions,
that's why we offer this free book.
- An call toll-free at 1-800-821-8383.
- Do you want me to go first
or do you wanna go first, Bree?
- You can go first.
(couple laughs)
- Audible reintroduced
this whole world to me.
- So many great stories
from amazing people,
it makes me wanna be better.
- To be able to connect
with the people's stories
that I'm listening to,
that's an inspiration.
- It's on during my commute,
it's on all the time.
- Doing the dishes.
- Working out.
- When I'm in the car.
- At bedtime.
- An Audible listener is someone
that wants to broaden their mind.
- [Customer] People who
are tired of listening
to the radio or music.
- To here her--
- It was--
- Speak those words--
- It was incredible.
- Unbelievable.
- With Audible Originals,
there's something for
almost every taste in there.
- Everything you ever wanted to hear.
- Well, I signed up for
getting a credit every month
and I started exploring books
that I normally wouldn't read.
- Our ability to empathize
through these stories,
with these stories, can
be transformational.
- It's my own thing that I can do for me.
- [Announcer] See what listening
to Audible can do for you.
Just text LISTEN14 to 500500.
(dramatic music)
- All right, we are getting
updated images coming out
of California right now and
that 7.1 magnitude earthquake,
which technically was 10 times more severe
than the one that preceded
it just 24 hours earlier.
Jeff Paul is in Ridgecrest,
California with the very latest.
Hey, Jeff.
- Yeah, Neil, and this
earthquake was felt far and wide.
I mean, we're right here,
the closest city near the epicenter
of this magnitude 7.1 earthquake,
but there are reports of people
as far north as Sacramento,
as far east as Phoenix, Arizona
and as far south as Mexico,
feeling some sort of rumbling due
to this particular earthquake
that happened just after
eight o'clock local time.
Now as you take a look at
some of this video here,
this is some video that my producer shot
as we were out grabbin' a bite to eat,
or at least trying to.
There was first a smaller
aftershock that was just minor,
but then a few minutes later,
that's when that 7.1 magnitude
earthquake rumbled through.
Yeah, you can hear the things
crashing in the restaurant,
you could hear people screaming
as they tried to take cover,
or find some safety.
And then shortly after that,
if you sorta got your wits about you,
we started hearing the sirens,
police going in every direction,
ambulances trying to respond
to the flurry of calls
that they got after this huge earthquake.
And then we saw fire off into the distance
and we know of at least one
structure that was destroyed,
we've heard about a few other fires caused
likely due to gas lines ruptures.
And a big part of that,
because of those fires
and because of the
uneasiness from residents,
some are choosing to sleep outside
and they slept outside last night.
We just caught up with one resident,
we asked her how she's gonna be,
sort of, living her life
moving forward, take a listen.
- If it happens, it happens.
But I'm not gonna sit
around and wait for it
and not do anything, I can't do that.
I've sat on the bench in our
picnic area for two nights now,
I'm not gonna do that.
I'm just gonna get on with
life and if it hits, it hits.
There's nothin' I can do to stop it,
there's nothin' I can do to forewarn me,
so I just gotta keep busy
so I don't think about it.
- And, Neil, experts warn
there will be more aftershocks
and there is a chance
there could be an even
bigger earthquake on the way.
Neil.
- Jeff Paul, thank you, my
friend, be safe yourself.
Jeff Paul in the middle of all of that.
By the way, we're keeping an eye on Iran,
it's already threatened to
retaliate over one of its tankers
seized by the British.
It's warning that it's prepared
to seize a British tanker.
Then what?
After this.
(dramatic marching music)
(app beeps)
(engine roars)
- [Announcer] From two stories to 20,
from ready apps to emergency response,
from your community to
a nationwide network,
the cleanup specialists at 1-800-SERVPRO,
everything under your
roof, everyone under ours.
Helping to make fire
and water damage like
it never even happened.
- Hi, I'm Dana Loesch from "The Dana Show"
and I wanna tell you about
a really simple thing
you can do that helps promote more energy
and supports healthy
blood pressure levels.
This is SuperBeets and I swear by it.
It gives me more healthy energy
to keep up with my hectic schedule
and you're gonna love
what it does for you, too.
- I can definitely use
a little more energy,
especially if it's from a
natural source, like beets.
- If I had something natural and healthy
that gave me energy, I'd be all in.
- Beets contain an essential nutrient
that makes them one
of the most heart-healthy
vegetables in nature.
SuperBeets concentrates that nutrient
into superfood crystals.
SuperBeets contains real food
that helps increase circulation
to get more oxygen flowing
throughout your body naturally.
It's supports healthy blood pressure
and gives you more healthy energy
to make the most of your day.
- [Announcer] Find out
how to get a free canister
with your first order, plus bonus gifts,
call 1-866-235-6901,
or go to trysuperbeets.com.
- I just mix a teaspoon
into a few ounces of water.
There's the natural apple
flavor, or black cherry flavor.
It tastes great!
- It's really yummy.
- It's a good flavor, I'm surprised.
- It doesn't taste like beets at all.
- I'll finish this, by the way.
- [Dana] What if you had more energy?
Imagine the possibilities.
- You feel strong and you feel healthy
and you feel like you
can accomplish anything.
- If I'm doing the
things that I need to do
to give me the energy, I feel better,
not only physically, but mentally.
- So do something good for your heart,
your circulation, your blood
pressure and your energy!
You'll love SuperBeets or your money back.
- [Announcer] Call now and find out
how to get a free canister
with your first order.
Plus, free indicator strips
that show how it's working
and shipping is free, too.
- This SuperBeets offer
isn't available in stores,
so call or go online right now.
- [Announcer] SuperBeets from Humann,
order your SuperBeets
today, call 1-866-235-6901,
or visit trysuperbeets.com.
- [Announcer] This is the
couple who wanted to get away,
who used Expedia to book
the vacation rental,
which led to the discovery
that sometimes a little
downtime can lift you right up.
Expedia, everything you need to go.
- Let's be honest, you only
talk about your insurance
when you complain about it.
(woman murmurs)
Good point.
That's why Esurance is
making the whole experience
surprisingly painless, so you
never have to talk about it
unless you're their spokesperson.
(toothbrushes clattering)
Esurance, it's surprisingly painless.
(dramatic music)
- All right, fast-moving
developments on Iran right now.
It is demanding the United
Kingdom release the oil tanker
it seized from Iran, it's right
now, I believe in Gibraltar.
This, as Iran says, it will
not negotiate with the U.S.
until sanctions are lifted.
With us is a former USS
Cole Commander Kirk Lippold
and, Commander, when it rains, it pours.
We understand that the
President just got off the phone
with Theresa May of Britain,
the soon-to-be outgoing
prime minister of Britain,
saying that, "The two countries are
"closely coordinating responses
to whatever Iran is planning
"and pushing for the
full denuclearization,
"separately, of North Korea,"
but obviously, in contact as
to judge what happens next.
You know this region very, very well
and you know what the
Iranians might be considering,
they're not adverse to seizing
personnel in the region,
as they did back in 2007,
when they stormed a British frigate
and, I believe, held about a
dozen men and women captive
for a while before releasing them.
So they're up to that and
they're apparently itching
to do that, or the same kinda thing.
What do you think?
- Well, I think, Neil, it's
a significant development
in the fact that the British
decided to seize this tanker.
Clearly, it was in violation,
not just of U.S. sanctions,
but more importantly, EU sanctions,
with that oil headed towards Syria.
That oil tanker carries
two million barrels of oil,
which equates to about 84 million gallons,
that was huge for the Syrian regime
to be able to support itself,
and the fact that that's
been cut off is good.
What Iran does next?
I think they should choose very wisely
because they do not want to
accidentally start something
that they may not be
able to stop or control.
- All right, we understand,
I might have misspoke,
Commander, that this conversation
between the President
and Theresa May was actually yesterday,
the details about it are
only coming to light today.
But they did talk about shared interests
in enforcing sanctions on Syria
to ensure Iran doesn't
obtain a nuclear weapon.
But with the Iranians ready to
exceed the uranium production
that would make such a thing more likely.
They're not payin' attention.
- Well, when you look at it,
Iran is getting squeezed much quicker
and much harsher than they anticipated
when President Trump put these
sanctions back into place.
If they in fact break
the cap that they claim
that they have with respect to the amount
they're allowed to have
for enriched uranium,
they're in violation of the agreement.
That now moves things into
a whole different category
and as a letter written
yesterday by Senators Cruz
and Rubio, and I believe one other,
they're looking and saying,
now that they violate that agreement,
we're now into the UN category
where the snapback sanctions
can in fact come into place.
This is now engaging the whole world
because Iran is not just
against the U.S. at this point,
now they're against the world.
And when Iran is doing that,
they're gonna find themselves
increasingly isolated,
not just from the U.S.,
but also our European allies
are going to begin to realize
that they need to not
only support the U.S.,
but more importantly support
the UN in what we're doing
to ensure that Iran never develops
that nuclear weapons capability.
- In the meantime, everyone's
waiting to see what they do
in response to this UK vessel move.
I was mentioning in 2007, seizing a vessel
that the Iranians claim was
not in international waters
but their waters,
but when it comes to the Strait of Hormuz,
or almost anything wet
nearby Iran, (laughs)
they declare that as their
land or their waters.
So how do you,
even argue for what are
internationally-recognized standards,
12 miles from a country's
shore is everybody's water.
- Well, it's a international waterway,
it's recognized under international law.
While the Iranians may make that claim,
it has absolutely no weight when it comes
to that international standard.
So people are going to be able
to continue to transit that waterway
and if Iran does interfere with it,
then the international
community at that point,
has an obligation to do whatever it takes,
diplomatically, economically
and if necessarily,
militarily to ensure that
the waterway stays open
for the pre-transit of
oil out of the Middle East
to keep the world's economies going.
- Commander, thank you very, very much,
good chatting with you again.
- As always, Neil, thank you.
- All right, in the meantime,
we have not forgotten about
the 2020 presidential race,
a lot of Democrats are already
knee-deep in fundraising
and a lot of them knee-deep in cash.
Who has the most?
It's a little early in the process,
but never too early to start
picking through the numbers
and what they might mean.
To do that, Gillian Turner in
Washington with the latest.
Hey, Gillian.
- Hey, good morning, Neil.
So the competition for funds, as you said,
is stiff this election cycle
and it got even tighter
among the top-tier Democrats
during the second quarter of this year,
according to the new numbers.
Candidates are on deadline to report Q2
to the FEC by July 15th, but
most made it in under the gun.
Let's take a look.
So far, Pete Buttigieg comes in tops
at $24.8 million in haul.
Joe Biden up next with $21.5 million.
Then Bernie Sanders with $18 million,
followed by Kamala
Harris with $12 million.
After Harris, though, the
drop-off's pretty steep.
Michael Bennet comes in next
with a $2.8 million haul
and says, "He's feelin' the heat."
- I haven't been running for
president for a long time,
I just got in the race.
So what I'm concerned about is making sure
that we continue to raise
the resources we need
to be able to be competitive
in the early states
of Iowa and New Hampshire.
- So these numbers matter, Neil,
because the candidates
will all need every dollar
they can get in order
to make it to round two,
the next Democratic
debate's comin' up soon.
The other thing, the number
that matters a lot here,
popularity, Biden's
still 10 points out ahead
of his Democratic colleagues,
even after falling a
little bit in the polls
after the last debate last week.
Neil.
- Gillian, thank you very, very much.
We are keeping track--
- You bet.
- Of where the candidates
are going to be today.
For example, Joe Biden,
we understand, is going
to be spending a good chunk
of time in South Carolina,
consider a must-win for
him to stabilize a campaign
that's been buffeted lately.
Republican South Carolina
Senator Tim Scott,
joining us right now.
Senator, good to have you.
- Good morning, Neil,
good to be back with you.
- Joe Biden's going to be in
your beautiful state today.
He has talked to the press
since of course that debate
where he's been sort
of universally panned,
that he can right the ship,
he's looking forward,
not looking backward,
how does he look in your
state on the Democratic side?
- You know, from my friends on the left,
they tell me that he's
still their preferred choice
because their goal is
to find the candidate
that they think will be the
most competitive against
our President Trump.
The fact is that I think
their goal of keeping Biden
as a front runner is an
important one for them,
but Kamala Harris is creeping up.
African-American voters are the majority
in the Democrat primary
and therefore her performance
against Joe Biden,
especially on a racial issue like busing,
has prompted more folks to
start taking a second look
at her and she is now
gaining within the state.
She has been behind in the
African-American community,
which has been quite
unusual and interesting.
Joe Biden's legacy as
the first vice president
of the first African-American
president has served him well.
But those numbers are startin'
to show a lot of cracks.
- You know, as you've
reminded in the past, Senator,
I just thought you were talking
book about South Carolina
in your pride of being the senator there,
but it has really turned a lot
of races in the past, hasn't it?
It was there that George Bush
put John McCain's surge to bed
and he went on, ultimately,
to win the Republican nomination in 2000,
putting him aside in South Carolina.
We saw something very, very
similar with Barack Obama,
an African-American who
had to win in that state
and did, handily over Hilary Clinton
on his route for the
nomination at the time.
I'm wondering if it will play
a similar role this go round?
- I think so, I call it
the miracle of the mo.
Momentum is a huge factor in politics
and the first in the South
primary state, South Carolina,
has proven to be the springboard
to presidential success
on the right as well as the left.
I think since 1980,
South Carolinians have
chosen the right president
on the Republican side all
times except for one time.
On the Democrat side, they've
had a lot of success, as well.
I think South Carolina is
poised to make the decision
for the Democrats this cycle.
It'll be interesting
to see who they choose.
I still think we're a long
way, of course, away from 2020,
but it'll be very interesting to see
who will stand toe-to-toe
with President Trump.
I like our odds right now, by the way.
I think we're in a very good
position, the economy's strong,
our international relationships
are getting stronger,
our president was very
presidential on Fourth of July.
There's no doubt that when
you look at the 2020 election,
it's gonna be a strong, powerful matchup,
but right now, I'm pretty
excited about where we are.
- You know, Senator, it's
very early and you remind me
it's very early so don't
get fixated on polls,
but are you surprised, given
the strength of the economy,
given the unexpected 224,000
job surge in the latest month
and all the good things that
go with that including markets
in and out of all-time highs,
that the President isn't
benefiting more from that?
What do you think is happening?
- Well, we're in a very polarized place
from a political
perspective, called America.
It has been challenging
for a very long time,
it's been getting worse, incrementally.
There's no doubt that we've
had a lot of distractions
from what should be,
as the old saying goes,
"The economy, stupid."
If we focus our attention
on the economic progress
that we've made, especially
in the most fragile,
economic Americans, we
would be celebrating.
Six million jobs created
since the tax reform,
half of those jobs have been occupied
by African-Americans and Hispanics.
We have a lot to celebrate,
but there have been so many
distractions durin' this cycle
that if we start focusing on the reality
of what matters to the average American,
how much more money am I taking home,
what is my likelihood for
success in this economy,
can my kids expect a
better America than I?
The answer is consistently yes.
The numbers bear that out,
but the narrative that we
hear consistently has nothing
to do with the reality,
it has to do with the
rhetoric of Washington.
That is, unfortunately,
distracting a lot of Americans
from what is, in fact, the
greatest economy we've seen
in more than three decades.
We've seen more progress
in race relations,
even right now I make this statement,
more progress in race relations,
more firsts than we've ever seen.
We should be excited to be Americans
and we should be excited to be
Americans right now in 2019.
There's so many distractions
trying to divide us
because if we stand united, we win,
if are divided, we are in jeopardy.
I think we're gonna get our act together
and I think the left has
been selling a rhetoric
as if it were reality.
We're gonna be able to
discern the difference
and create the contrast so
that the average American,
whether they vote for Republicans or not,
that's not the question,
is America better off under
the conservative principles
and policies put in place?
The answer is resoundingly, yes.
- But do you think the President
risked torpedoing that,
Senator, by this ongoing
trade riff with China?
Now tariffs have really
not had a chance to kick in
since so many goods were
already on store shelves.
I believe they were going
to kick in when stuff,
mid-shipment, would get
to the United States.
So the real impact of
that hasn't been felt
and the President argues
that he likes tariffs anyway,
that a lot of money is coming in.
But average Americans pay those tariffs
and I'm wondering if you feel
he's out of step with that,
or out of sync with that,
and it's gonna cost him?
- Well, I like to break the
tariff conversation down
into multiple categories.
When you think about China,
China's goal is to steal the future,
which would imperil American progress.
President Trump's approach with China is a
necessary altercation so that
we can restore confidence
in our workforce and create
the best future going forward
from a technological standpoint.
The goal for their IP theft is simply
to steal the future of work.
We're not gonna let that happen.
- So tariffs are worth it--
- I applaud--
- In that regard to you?
- The President's approach.
- You agree with the
President's tariffs are worth it
to send that message,
but do you think tariffs
are a good thing, period,
that if--
- No, no--
- If this isn't settled,
it's gonna boomerang on Republicans?
- No question, there's
no doubt that today,
if you look at the six or seven states
that you were talking
about earlier in the show,
the wage gains in those states
that tariffs get put in jeopardy,
their wage growths have
outstripped the wage growths
that we're celebrating at 3.1%.
Some states have had four,
five, 6% wage growth,
that's exciting news,
especially in those sectors,
but the truth is
that the overall tariff
conversation is not
in the best interest of
Americans, without any question.
I put the asterisk out there for China,
because it's a very different
conversation we're having.
We're using tariffs in trade as a means
of resetting tectonic shift in the plates
on our relationships.
But when you think about the USMCA,
when you think about Europe,
we have to make sure
that we don't go too far.
The 232 auto tariffs is a classic example,
where I have pushed back,
because I think they create
headwinds throughout the South.
- Senator, it's always a
pleasure catching up with you,
be well.
- Thank you, sir.
- All right, Senator Tim
Scott of South Carolina,
joining us out of Mount
Pleasant, South Carolina.
We mentioned the President,
he says he's looking into
using an executive order
to get that citizenship question
back on the 2020 Census.
Now forget about your
politics, is that even legal?
After this.
- Any time Philly plays New
York, it's a like a lit fuse.
Only a matter of time
before we get the fireworks.
Led by one of the game's biggest stars,
Bryce is ready to make
his mark on this rivalry.
- [Commentator] Absolutely crushed!
- [Announcer] The other by a rookie phenom
with power you have to see to believe.
- [Commentator] Alonzo, gets into one!
Gone!
(dramatic music)
- [Announcer] Phillies, Mets,
tonight at 7:00 Eastern on FOX
and the FOX Sports App.
- Meeting people is my life.
I had to be careful how
wide I would open my mouth
because I was embarrassed
to show my teeth.
It was time to do something for myself
that was gonna be permanent.
- [Announcer] The
ClearChoice one day approach
is making dental implants a reality
for people all over the country
who suffer from missing or failing teeth.
- I felt like I was the
most important person
on Earth to them.
- Bill came in, bad
teeth, discomfort, pain.
We needed to get him into a
smile that he felt confident in.
We have expertise that he
might not find anywhere else,
all in one location.
- [Bill] The next day, I had a new smile.
Couldn't wait to show some folks,
it's amazing what a smile
can do for a person.
- [Announcer] Discover
why this is so much more
than another dental procedure,
it's a true life-changer.
With over 30,000 new smiles and counting,
we're lifting spirits and
confidence all over America.
Schedule your free consultation today,
we'll even talk about financing options.
- [Bill] I'm eatin' corn on the cob.
I had the best smile
I'd ever had in my life.
- [Announcer] Call ClearChoice today.
- [Announcer] While
serving overseas in 2007,
Staff Sergeant Mark Lalli's
helicopter went down
in a life-altering crash.
- Of the 11 onboard,
only five of us survived.
I had to relearn how to speak,
how to eat and how to walk.
How to do things that we all
take for granted every day.
- [Announcer] Thankfully,
Wounded Warrior Project was there
for support.
- One of the first events
with Wounded Warrior Project
that I was involved with,
I met my future wife.
The first time she was over at the house,
she saw my walker and she
said, "Hey, do you use that?"
I said, "If we ever get to the point
"where we're gonna get married,
"I'll be on my feet, I promise you that."
- When he told me he was
gonna walk down the aisle,
it made me feel special and flattered.
I just knew I was gonna marry him.
- I had to work as hard as I
could for as long as I had to
in order to make that happen.
I'm so thankful for
Wounded Warrior Project
for getting me where I
could meet my future wife
and walk down the aisle for her.
Gave me a life worth living.
- Being detected was not an option.
If I was recognized, the
whole operation was blown.
The element of surprise was imperative.
- Wow, (laughs) he won't
even recognize you!
- Seriously, I don't even
recognize myself! (laughs)
And thanks to my cashRewards
credit card from Navy Federal
with never expiring rewards,
it's gonna be a killer honeymoon!
- [Soldier] Woo, Maui!
(woman laughs)
- Boom!
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Navy Federal Credit Union,
our members are the mission.
(dramatic music)
- [Reporter] Are you going
to issue an executive order
on the census?
- We're thinking about doing
that, it's one of the ways.
We have four or five ways we can do it.
We can also add an addition on
so we can start the printing
now and maybe do an addendum
after we get a positive decision.
So we're working on a lot of things,
including an executive order.
- All right, the President
says he's looking into ways
of adding that citizenship
question after all to the census,
including, as he said
there, an executive order.
Would that hold up in court?
It's not quite that black and white,
but who better to pick it apart
than attorney extraordinaire,
Mercedes Colwin.
- Hi, Neil.
- So as I understand, Mercedes,
the Supreme Court didn't
reject the argument
as much as say the administration,
through the Commerce Department,
didn't give it a compelling
enough case, right?
- And didn't really give the explanation.
So I'm going to step back to 2013
because they had a similar case
regarding the Voting Rights Act.
It had nothing to do with the census
or the citizenship issue, but
it had to do with that law.
Chief Justice Roberts, who
was the Chief Judge then,
said we're gonna step away.
The federal government's gonna step away
and let the states deal
with the electoral process,
they can do the legislation
at the local level.
So basically,
the governance on the
Federal's part, step back.
Now 2019, now the federal
government steps in
and says, hey, we want
to help with respect
to the Voting Rights Act,
which what it did was,
made sure that the individuals could vote,
regardless of discrimination.
If you go back decades ago,
that's where it germinated.
It started with allowing
individuals to vote,
regardless of their race.
Well now, so the Chief Judge Roberts says,
why are you going back
to the Voting Rights Act,
which we already ruled in 2013,
let the states deal with it,
why is the Federal government
stepping in now in 2019
and say, well, we're going
to assist in the promulgation
of the Voting Rights Act,
make sure that it's enforced properly,
make sure that there's no discrimination,
make sure that the districts
that have a high number
of individuals that are of color
or have the appropriate numbers
of representation in Congress,
when we've already ruled that
the states can deal with this?
- So what kind--
- So that's--
- Of compelling argument--
- The difference on this.
- Do they need to make to win
over this particular judge,
who has to be won over?
- Sure, frankly, just
step forward and say,
look, we wanna look at the districting.
Just come straight out and say,
"It's not so much discrimination
"because we know, Chief
Judge, that your ruled
"on letting the local government
deal with this in 2013,
"we're looking to make sure
"that there's appropriate
levels of representation."
So if their districts,
and this is what a lot
of the DOJ members have been
writing about in these op-eds,
have said, "Why don't
you just come forward
"and say hey, we might need this.
"We might need greater
numbers of representation,
"but in order for there
to be greater numbers
"of representation in Congress or less,
"we need to know how
many U.S. citizens are
"in particular jurisdictions
around the country."
- So why wasn't there a tenth the fuss
when the question was taken out?
'Cause it used to be
a staple in the census
then it was taken out under
the Obama administration.
I don't remember anyone saying boo then,
so why is it a big deal
putting it back in?
- Well, I think what Chief Judge wanted,
someone to come forward and say,
hey, it was about districting and yes,
we're gonna talk not only
about the districting issue and how much,
it's also the infrastructure.
You've got $980 billion that--
- So they're thinking--
- You're going to give--
- There might be something--
- Around the country.
- Sinister afoot here
and they wanna prove or disprove that.
- Exactly, especially in the history
of the Voting Rights Act back in 2013.
I think--
- That's interesting.
- If you've got the same Chief Judge,
so he's looking and saying--
- I didn't know that.
- Just come forward.
Can I say a quick hi to my mom?
She's watching, hi, Roslyn!
Love ya, Mom!
- That's nice.
Was it, Roslyn, she's a very smart woman.
- Roslyn Stern, she's amazing!
- She is, indeed.
(Mercedes laughs)
All right, Mercedes,
thank you very, very much.
Tom Homan, the former acting ICE Director,
his read on all of this
and what this means
if the President can't
get that question in.
After this.
(phone rings)
- Uh-oh, looks like
someone's still nervous
about buyin' a new house.
- Is it that obvious?
- Yes, it is.
You know, maybe you'd
worry less if you got Geico
to help with your homeowner's insurance.
- I didn't know Geico helps
with homeowner's insurance.
- Yeah, they've been doin' it for years.
(stress balls squeaking)
What are you doin'?
Big Steve?
(stress balls clattering)
- Thanks, man.
- There he is.
[Announcer] Get to know
Geico and see how much
you could save on homeowner's
and renter's insurance.
- Introducing Nutrisystem's
July Fourth Sale!
Save 50%, yes, 50%.
- [Announcer] It's your
favorite foods made healthier!
Perfectly balanced to put
your body in fat-burning mode.
Lose up to 13 pounds
and seven inches overall
in your first month.
- I'm Marie and I lost 50
pounds with Nutrisystem.
- I lost 60 pounds with Nutrisystem.
- I lost 30 pounds with Nutrisystem.
- Count, measure, meetings,
not with Nutrisystem.
- [Announcer] Order your
28-day plan right now.
You'll get specially-designed meals.
- The food comes right to
your door and it tastes great.
You get the right foods
in the right portions,
so you'll learn how to
keep the weight off.
- [Announcer] Plus, one
week of high-protein shakes
with probiotics to help
shrink your belly, free!
- There's even a money-back guarantee.
- [Announcer] For a limited time,
save 50% off every program.
- Grab this special offer right
now and start losing today!
- [Announcer] Go online or
call 877-236-FIT9 right now
to save 50%!
- [Man] Who!
(upbeat music)
- I like to plan my activities
before I take a trip
so by the time I get there,
I can just enjoy the ride!
(engine hums)
With TripAdvisor, it's easy to discover
over 100,000 bookable things to do.
From walking tours in Rome,
to wine tastings in Tuscany
and if you like what you see,
you can book it with ease.
Just another way
TripAdvisor helps you make
your trip a masterpiece!
- Who!
- [Owl] Read reviews, check hotel prices,
book things to do, TripAdvisor.
- [Announcer] Tonight,
it's Fourth of July weekend
and Jesse wants you to know
what makes America great.
Dean Cain and Charlie Kirk join the show
for a discussion you can't
miss on "Watters' World".
- [Announcer] On INSP Channel 364,
(gun bangs)
this summer--
- Let's make some music!
- [Announcer] Belongs to the Duke.
- You're drawing quite a crowd.
- [Announcer] Tomorrow at 2:00.
Against impossible odds
(gun bangs)
they'll uphold the law.
John Wayne, Dean Martin, Ricky Nelson
and Angie Dickinson star--
- He'll live through it.
- Now you do the same.
- [Announcer] "Rio Bravo",
tomorrow at 2:00 p.m.
- Look out!
(gun bangs)
- [Announcer] John Wayne
movies all month long.
Don't miss The Duke Days of Summer.
- Come and get it, boy!
- [Announcer] On INSP Channel 364.
- [Announcer] Get ready
for this summer's biggest,
turbo-charged blockbuster.
- You ready, buddy?
(suspenseful music)
- [Announcer] "Battle
of the '80s Super Cars
"with David Hasselhoff",
featuring a race between
the Hoff, Erik Estrada
and Dirk Benedict.
(tires squealing)
"Evel Live 2", with Axell
Hodges, Vicki Golden,
plus, "Chuck Norris' Epic
Guide to Military Vehicles".
(explosion booms)
- Horse power and fire power.
(gun bangs)
[Announcer] Car Week begins
tomorrow at 8:00 on History.
(dramatic music)
- All right, we've Tom Homan here,
the former acting ICE
director, he's gonna talk about
this push the administration
has to go through
with these deportations,
more on that in a sec.
But I did wanna give
Tom a chance to respond
to what Mercedes Colwin
was talking about regarding
of this question in the census
that the administration wants
to push by executive order
to make sure you can still
ask are you a legal citizen
of the United States.
Where do you think this is going, Tom?
- Well, I hope the
administration succeeds in it
for a couple of reasons.
Number one, don't we wanna know
how many illegal aliens
are in the United States?
I mean, if they're talking
about immigration reform,
free medical care, pathways to citizenship
for people here illegally for a while,
don't we wanna know
what that population is?
I think that'd be the basis
of makin' some of these decisions.
And second of all, I
don't think representation
in the House of Representatives,
or the Electoral College
that elects our president,
should be based on people
who are here illegally.
So I think it's good
for a couple of reasons.
- So, let me switch
gears a little bit here.
Regardless of how that works,
the administration still says
it's going to pursue these
deportations, legal deportations,
the kind that went under Barack Obama
in cases already adjudicated and judged,
"All right, you have to go back to Mexico,
"or Honduras, or Guatemala," wherever,
and it's going to start soon,
the President didn't indicate how soon.
How do you think that's going to go?
- Look, it's going to be controversial,
but I think it needs to be done.
It's not a question should it
be done, it has to be done.
And as you said, Neil, I did this
when I was the executive
associate director at ICE.
I ran a national operation
called Operation Border Guarding
back in 2015, when we
went and sought out those
who had final orders,
specifically family units,
and we arrested some family units,
had final orders by an immigration judge,
we put 'em on airplanes and sent 'em home
and the borders numbers went down
because we showed there's a
consequence to deterrence.
If a final order by an immigration
judge, after due process,
doesn't mean anything,
then there's no integrity in the system,
just open the border
up and let everybody in
because there's no consequence anymore,
there's no law, there's no
rule governing who can come in,
who can come into the
United States legally.
- Tom, what do you do
for the illegals here
and protected in sanctuary
cities, towns, or states?
They're gonna do
everything in their power,
these cities, towns, or states
to makes sure that the
Feds can't get in there.
- Well, they're not gonna stops the Feds
from doin' their job.
Look, they can not assist,
which they've done,
or they do what the Oakland mayor did
and give 'em a heads up, "ICE is in town,"
but the men and women--
- But that's illegal--
- Who are in ICE are gonna do their job.
- The head's up is an illegal act, right?
- Not only that,
but you know you had a
congressman the other day,
Ocasio-Cortez talkin' about
how people should take 'em
into their homes.
Look, aiding and abetting,
harboring an illegal alien's a felony,
so you know, ICE is goin'
to take this seriously.
These people've had their due process
at great tax payer expense.
They've been ordered by a judge to go home
and if you and I can
ignore a judge's order,
what would happen to us, Neil?
This has to be done.
As controversial as it
is, if we don't do it,
then we might as well just
blow the whole system up
and open the border up,
because we have no security,
we have no sovereignty,
we have no rule over
all the country anymore.
If people wanna step in the way of ICE,
then look for further action from ICE.
It's a crime to impede federal
law enforcement officers.
- The law's on your
side in this case, Tom,
there's no doubt about that,
but of course, images can play
havoc in the middle of this.
The reason why I'm thinkin',
I'm old enough to remember
the Elian Gonzalez case
when he was seized from a home
and ultimately sent back to Cuba.
And was those images, legal
as they were to retrieve him,
that stuck in American's heads
during the Clinton administration.
That's going to be inevitable,
the images of ICE agents,
rammin' on doors to try to get people,
say, "All right, you're
arrested, you have to go back,"
how is that all gonna go down?
- Well, look, to those people
who are gonna push that message,
I think you need to ask 'em a question,
"What is your option?
"What do you wanna do?"
Because if there's no
integrity in the system,
if people can come here
to the Unites States,
they can enter illegally
and get to stay forever
'cause we're not brave
enough to enforce the law,
that's gonna send a bad message
to the rest of the world,
come here, violate our laws,
the facilities will still be overcrowded.
If the message we wanna send
to the rest of the world is,
come here with a child, you
can even have due process
at great tax payer expense,
billions of dollars,
and when the Federal
judge orders you removed,
you don't have to leave
because it's uncomfortable
to arrest you and make you leave,
then we're never gonna
solve the border crisis.
And this isn't just about
enforcin' the law, Neil,
this is about saving lives.
Children are dying entering this country,
31% of women are being raped.
We gotta send the message, it's not okay,
and we're bankrollin'
criminal organizations
that are smuggling these people.
It's just not about enforcin'
laws, it's about saving lives
and takin' money out of
criminal organizations' hands.
It's the right thing to
do, as sad, as unfortunate,
sometimes enforcin' law is,
it doesn't mean we ignore it.
- I'd be remiss if I didn't
mention these Facebook postings
of a present, maybe former, CBP workers
who had disparaging comments they made
about those who they were
protecting at these facilities,
towards those who visited them.
Do you believe, it's proven,
that many of them said the things
they were alleged to have said,
that they should be terminated?
- I wanna wait and see what
the investigation shows,
but I've been told that, from my sources,
there's only several people
that posted things to that extreme.
And of course, they need to be dealt with,
that's not the border patrol I
know and I think it distracts
from the fine work the
border patrols are doin'.
But I'll say this,
at what point, when you
go to work every day,
you're being called a Nazi, a racist,
that you're makin' women
drink outta toilets,
which is total crap,
and when you go to work
and you hear these things,
you get beaten down every day,
you get pushed in the corner every day,
at what point does your spirit get broken,
you may do some things
that you probably shouldn't have done?
I'm not makin' excuses for anybody,
but these men and women
of the border patrol,
they're doin' a great job in
a very difficult circumstances
and the vast, vast majority of
'em are doin' the right thing
for their nation, and if a
few people step outta line,
they should be dealt with absolutely.
- All right, Tom Holman,
thank you very, very much.
Good seeing you again.
- [Tom] Good seeing you, Neil.
All right, to show ya that
this is indeed a world-wide problem,
again those who tried
to flee to safer shores,
an Italian rescue ship with 46
migrants on board has docked
in the Italian port city of Lampedusa,
against an explicit ban on refugees.
This isn't just in this country,
folks, this is world wide.
More after this.
- When I book at hilton.com,
I get to select my room
from the floor plan,
free Wi-Fi and the price match guarantee.
- So with Hilton there is no catch.
- (laughs) Yeah, the only
catch is I'm never leaving.
(woman laughs)
No, I'm serious, I live here now.
Book at hilton.com and get the
Hilton Price Match Guarantee.
- What if there was something
that can reduce body fat,
boost mood, get rid of
wrinkles, tighten saggy skin
and make you look and
feel decades, not years,
but decades younger?
I'm talking about human
growth hormone, or HGH.
Finally, there's SeroVital.
- [Announcer] In a clinical trial,
SeroVital has been shown to
boost your HGH naturally,
up to an astonishing 682%.
- SeroVital gave me my youth back.
- [Announcer] SeroVital, available at ULTA
and smarter retailers nationwide.
- Look, cleaning the outside
of your windows is a real chore.
(woman screams)
And who wants to climb a dangerous ladder
just to get to the second floor?
(woman sighs)
Not anymore!
Hi, Jon Florell, the Fuller Brush man
and this is Full Crystal,
from the Fuller Brush Company.
The fastest, easiest way to
clean all of your windows
in minutes, not days.
Just add the cleaning crystals,
attach it to any garden
hose and away ya go!
The secret is in the
Fuller cleaning crystals
that dissolve dust, dirt,
pollen and grime in no time!
And here's the best part,
you don't have to remove your screens
because Full Crystal cleans them, too!
Watch what I'm gonna do.
This screen may look clean,
but look how Full Crystal
blasts away the dust,
pollen, dirt and grime
while it cleans your
window at the same time.
And that'll save you a ton of time!
Look, even with the ladder,
you couldn't reach that window.
But with the Full Crystal power sprayer,
you can clean windows up to 27 feet high.
Simply aim, spray and walk away,
leaving your windows
spot free, streak free
and with both feet securely on the ground.
For a clean so clear, your
windows will virtually disappear!
Plus, it's completely safe
for all of your plants,
lawns, shrubs and flowers.
Call or go online now
to order the complete Full Crystal system
with enough cleaning
crystals for up to 20 windows
for the factory direct
price of just $19.99.
But order right now and we'll
double the cleaning crystals,
enough for up to 40 windows,
just pay a separate fee.
Fuller Cleaning Crystal
are made in the USA
and remember, it's from
the Fuller Brush Company,
so your satisfaction is 100% guaranteed.
Call or go online to buyfullcrystal.com.
That's buyfullcrystal.com.
And ask about Full Exterior,
to easily clean dirt
and grime from all around the exterior
of your house in no time.
Order now!
- We need to talk.
You and I are busy people
and some days there's just
not enough time, am I right?
Well Takl helps you make
time for what you love
and find help for what you don't.
Simply download Takl and
choose the pre-priced job
that you need and voila,
an approved-provider is at
your doorstep the same day.
So whether it's assembling furniture
or just mowing the yard,
Takl is the proven solution
that fits your schedule.
That's Takl.
- With all that USAA offers,
why go with anybody else?
We know their rates are good,
we know that they're always
gonna take care of us.
- It was an instant savings
and I shoulda changed a long time ago.
- We're the Tenneys and
we're USAA members for life.
- [Announcer] Call USAA to
start saving on insurance today.
(hard rock music)
- [Chris] They're gonna come after you.
- [Joe] Sure they're gonna come after me.
- We're you prepared for
them you to come after you?
- I was prepared for them to come after me
but I wasn't prepared for the
person coming at me the way
she came at.
- All right, Joe Biden trying to explain
his awful performance in that debate
and Kamala Harris going
too far too quickly,
especially raising a busing issue
that goes back to the 1970s.
Now his supporters are
questioning, if he wasn't prepared
for that, is he prepared for the job
of President of the United States at all?
All In Together CEO Lauren
Leader back with us,
Republican strategist Joseph Pinon
and the host of "Sincerely
Kat" on FOX Nation, Kat Timf.
So, Lauren, let me ask you,
it just seems like a lot
of excuse making here.
- (sighs) You know, you ask two questions,
"Is he prepared to be president?"
and I think he certainly
is incredibly qualified,
but that's not how you
get to be president.
I mean the fact is that
there are 25 candidates
that are gonna come after him.
Sitting at the top of the polls is
actually not a great
place to be this early on
because it opens up a million doors
to scrutinize every piece of his record.
And look, younger voters are paying
very close attention to this,
younger voters and women, particularly,
are really watching to ask--
- [Neil] Has he lost
them since this debate?
- No, I don't think he's lost them,
but I think he's gonna have
a serious enthusiasm problem
if he can't turn some of this around.
And I think that's what
candidates like Harris
and others saw as an opening,
this sort of tone deafness on some issues
that are very powerful and
real for younger voters,
for minority voters, for women voters.
He has a very strong support
in the African-American community,
he's polling super well in
places like South Carolina,
but I think she wants to chip away at that
and that's exactly why she went after him
on that particular issue.
- Joseph, the President has not said much
about Kamala Harris
and normally that could
be a sign he's worried,
or it could be that he hopes
that Joe Biden rights the ship
because he's got all these monikers,
like Sleepy Joe--
- Sleepy Joe.
- And all this other stuff.
But what is goin' there?
- Look, I think that the
President recognizes,
as most of us do, that if you're talkin'
about strictly demographics,
Joe Biden causes the greatest threat
to his pathway to reelection.
I think what a lot of people--
- [Neil] What did he
keep stumbling like this?
All of a sudden he's not such a threat.
- Well, I think, look, he
has to come out swingin',
I think that in order to
hold on to his support,
particularly in communities of color,
he actually must be prepared to lose it.
I think that that means that
he has to protect his record
and not that I'm givin' them advice,
but say to look, for the
record, busing didn't work,
we've got schools today
that they're more segregated
than they were during Jim Crow South.
You know, he has to be prepared to say
that this woman, who is a
senator, who I have respect for,
came out with an attack on an issue
which she basically agrees with me on,
for the purpose of selling t-shirts.
- [Kat] Just needs to be prepared period.
I just don't--
- And he wasn't.
- I don't understand--
- He was prepared
for questions about whether you pal around
with segregationists, but
apparently not for busing.
- What was he doing then?
Because if you think about it, back then,
he's been out there a
little bit more lately,
but right before the debates,
he wasn't making public appearances,
he was doing, I don't know,
because he didn't look
prepared for the debate either.
I don't know if he was watchin' cat videos
on the internet or playin'
Candy Crush, takin' naps,
I don't know, but I don't understand
why you wouldn't be prepared--
- [Neil] Wouldn't that be cool if he was--
- He was--
- Like up there and actually
playing Candy Crush.
- Maybe he's addicted
to Candy Crush.
Maybe I just figured it out and
that's why he did so poorly.
I don't know, but I would
think that if you were gonna be
in front of millions
of people watching you,
you'd wanna do your homework.
Just to not embarrass yourself.
- In fairness, look, he's
has a lifetime of experience
and I'm sure he counted--
- He admitted
he wasn't prepared, though.
- On that.
And he admitted he wasn't--
- He admitted that.
- Look, he clearly had a bad night.
The reality is, is it
is incredibly difficult
to sit at the top of the polls
when you've got 24 people
behind you chasing you
and who are gonna dig into
every piece of his record--
- 'Cause look at Jeb Bush,
he was at the top--
- Yeah, I mean--
- Of the polls and it evaporated.
- It not a good place--
- Please clap.
- To be this early.
Yeah, I mean, please clap.
(Kat laughs)
I mean he sorta had that moment.
It's not a place to be and
I've said from the beginning,
I think his numbers are
gonna continue to fall
before they come back up.
Look, Democrats have an
enormous field of choices,
an enormous set of issues to explore.
There is a whole new generation of voters
who don't have the history
with him, that don't feel a set
of connections with him--
- Yeah, they don't know it
and like a passing ship in the night.
One of the things he said--
- They don't.
Listen, the key to this election,
it's not just about the
primary vote, right,
what's gonna turn 2020
for the Democrats is going
to be enthusiasm and energy of new voters,
Gen Z, Gen Y--
- And they don't have it
for him.
- Women and people of color,
they have no history with him.
- Let me ask you about where
the path of the party lies
and Joe Biden was saying
of Representative
Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez,
I'll ask you about this Joe,
"She's bright and brilliant,
but too far left."
In other words saying, our gains have come
from more moderate
victories, and he's right.
Of the 40, I guess, who
were elected to the House,
I think 32 fit the moderate label,
that might be over-generalizing it
and not the Ocasio-Cortez label.
But did in so saying that,
did he kinda bury himself?
- No, I think that he's
speakin' the truth.
Now having said that, that
give him some trepidations
and difficulties getting
through this primary process,
but the fact remains is that only people
who are talkin' about this
Democratic party expanding left,
faster than the universe expands,
are people who live in districts
that they couldn't lose
even if they are runnin'
against a guy who--
- [Neil] So you are arguing that he,
when he says he's worried
about the party moving too,
too far left and promises
Medicare-for-all,
college education, college
debt, rights for illegals
and all that, that that isn't even in sync
with his Democratic base?
- I would say that it's 100% the fact
that he's basically on
the post of the party,
more so than what AOC's talkin' about.
That's why he's the front-runner,
in spite of his performance.
- I don't know if that's true.
- I don't know, I don't know about that
because look at after the
debates, he lost so much support
and Elizabeth Warren
gained a lot of support
and she is very, very progressive.
Plus, we also know that
primary voters tend
to be more progressive than people votin'
in general elections, so
we might wind up with the--
- Well, Republican primary voters tend
to be more conservative in that, right?
- Absolutely, yes.
- He's tryin' to run a general
election during a primary
and that's--
- And he hasn't won it yet.
He tried to equivocate on
that in the CNN interview,
that he doesn't want to be
presumptuous, et cetera,
which he clearly--
- Well, you want the Democrat
to win, whoever it is, right?
So do you get concerned
that they could be
spoiling it for themselves,
offering things and promises
and proposals that even
the Democratic voter
in this country doesn't support?
- You know, I really don't, I don't
and I don't because I think, look,
what is the point of a primary
in an environment like this?
It's a battle of ideas.
Ultimately, there's gonna
be ideas far to the left,
somewhere in the middle
and then they're gonna land somewhere
that's more in line with
the American people,
but I think it's a valuable process.
That's why I actually,
I don't agree with a lot
of the people on the left
who say we need to cull
the field so quickly.
There is a benefit to the whole country
when you've got a lot of really qualified,
experienced people debating
a whole set of ideas
about the future of the country.
So I think it will swing
back towards the center
as we get closer to the nomination,
but I think he's wrong
to sort of hold this.
Kat's right, he's gonna
alienate a lot of the people
that he really needs to turn
out for him in the primaries
if he's gonna win.
- I disagree.
I think that, again,
Joe Biden is playin' a game right now
where he believes that's
he's goin' to depend
on reliable voters.
Reliable voters are older
voters, they're older,
black voters, those are the
people that he's talkin' to,
his performance, notwithstandin'.
I think that he fell because
he didn't do a very good job.
- He had a bad night.
- He kinda stunk.
- [Kat] An understatement that
he didn't do a very good job.
- [Neil] Maybe he's
just a lousy candidate.
- But I think if you look at it,
if look at Elizabeth Warren rising,
I think that she's rising, not
on the strength of Joe Biden,
but on the strengths of the fact
that people remember remember it now
that she is the original person
when it comes to those
trillion dollar giveaways,
she is the one with the plans
towards Bernie's rhetoric
and I think that you see
Kamala Harris going after Biden
because she realizes that her
path to getting more money
and her path to actually
rise in the polls goes
directly through Joe Biden.
- Well that's the danger
of bein' on top, right.
- Yep.
- The danger of bein' on top.
Guys, I wanna thank you,
thank you for coming in
on a very hot Saturday,
we appreciate that.
In the meantime, do any of you remember,
maybe I'm old enough, just
to read the history books,
when Franklin Roosevelt was trying
to pack the Supreme Court?
Is this president trying to do the same
with the Federal Reserve?
We connect, you decide.
(dramatic marching music)
(app beeps)
(engine roars)
- [Announcer] From two stories to 20,
from ready apps to emergency response,
from your community to
a nationwide network,
the cleanup specialists at 1-800-SERVEPRO,
everything under your
roof, everyone under ours.
Helping to make fire
and water damage like
it never even happened.
- [Announcer] These days,
you can't go anywhere
without your phone in your hand.
So to keep it secure
when your hands are busy,
WeatherTech invented the CupFone.
With removable cups, the
CupFone fits any size cup holder
and adjusts to secure
virtually any sized phone.
Tilts for perfect viewing,
even allows easy access while charging.
So if you're driving,
boating or even golfing,
it fits perfectly.
Whatever you drive,
whatever phone you have,
CupFone is the perfect fit.
Order your American-made CupFone
today at weathertech.com.
- [Announcer] Inflammation may cause
everyday joint discomfort.
Turmeric supports healthy
inflammation response
due to physical overexertion.
Qunol provides superior
absorption compared
to regular tumeric.
(box booms)
Qunol, the better turmeric.
(bell dings)
(stomach rumbles)
♪ When you have nausea,
heartburn, indigestion, ♪
♪ Upset stomach ♪
♪ Diarrhea ♪
- [Announcer] Try new Pepto liquid caps
for fast relief and ultra coating.
♪ Nausea, heartburn, indigestion, ♪
♪ Upset stomach, diarrhea ♪
- [Announcer] Get powerful relief
with new Pepto-Bismol liquid caps.
- [Announcer] Their quest
for a record fourth World
Cup comes down to the final.
- [Commentator] Header!
Goal!
(crowd roars)
- [Announcer] It's now all or nothing
for the Stars and Stripes
as Megan Rapinoe and
Alex Morgan lead the U.S.
- Unstoppable!
- Against the Netherlands.
- [Commentator] Spectacular!
- [Announcer] The reigning champs put
their legacy on the line.
- [Commentator] Goal!
- [Announcer] One last time.
The World Cup final,
coverage begins tomorrow
at 10 a.m. Eastern on FOX
and the FOX Sports App.
(Jason snores)
(alarm beeps)
(lively electronic dance music)
(clock bangs)
(upbeat music)
(toaster clinks)
(dryer hums)
(tie rack buzzes)
(door slams)
(dog barks)
(sitar strums)
(seat belt sensor sings)
("Beverly Hills 90210" rock music)
(uplifting music)
- [Announcer] This is the
couple who wanted to get away,
who used Expedia to book
the vacation rental,
that led to the ride,
(gulls calling)
which took them to the place,
where they discovered that sometimes,
a little downtime can lift you right up.
Flights, hotels, cars,
activities, vacation rentals,
Expedia, everything you need to go.
- All right, I don't think
the President is still a fan
of the Federal Reserve,
blasting in a two-part
Tweet saying in part,
"Strong jobs report, low
inflation and other countries
"around the world doing anything possible
"to take advantage of the United States,
"knowing that our Federal
Reserve doesn't have clue!
"They raised rates too soon, too often
"and tightened while others
did just the opposite."
Then, to rub a little
more salt in the wound,
saying that, "Our most
difficult problem is not
"our competitors, it is
the Federal Reserve!"
Joining me now, the former Fed nominee
and Heritage Foundation
Chief Economist Steve Moore.
He will not let go of
this, is that hurting him?
What do you think?
- Well, let me start by saying this,
when I was driving in this morning, Neil,
I was thinking that,
I think you and I are about the same age,
this may be the best economy
we've seen in our lifetime.
And when you've got the
lowest unemployment rate
in 50 years, you've got no
inflation, you got rising wages,
you got 7 1/2 million more
jobs than people to fill them,
the stock market is now officially up 50%
since Donald Trump was elected--
- So he's blaming the Fed
that it could be a lot higher
and by the way, I had no
idea you were 39, touche.
(Steve laughs)
But what do you make of that--
- You're a little younger
than I am! (laughs)
- He just won't let go.
- But no, look,
the reason I say that, Neil,
as prefaced your question,
isn't it about time we started giving
this guy the benefit of the doubt.
I mean, I remember during the
campaign, workin' for Trump,
and people said if
Donald Trump is elected,
we're gonna get us a
second Great Depression,
now we got the best economy in 50 years.
And so, I think Trump, I've
talked to him so many times
about this, Neil, he is
frustrated by the Fed.
That's one of the reasons he nominated me,
I think the Fed is too tight, as well.
I think that the Fed--
- [Neil] Well now he's naming two people--
- I know, Judy Shel--
- The interpretation is that
they'll do his bidding and
that they agree with him,
what do you think of that?
- They share his vision of the economy.
Here's the problem with the Fed
and this has been a
problem not just recently,
but for 30 years.
The Fed believes that if you
get too many people working,
too much growth, wages rising,
somehow they have to snuff that out.
And Donald Trump, from
the first time I met him,
he said, "We're gonna
get this economy moving
"at three to 4% per year,
way up from what we had under Obama,"
and his frustration is, Neil,
every time we get a good jobs report,
or every time the growth
comes up where wages rise,
the Fed wants to pull it back.
I think that's wrong-headed,
we can grow this economy
without inflation faster and
Trump is right about this--
- Do you worry, though, and
I get where you're coming
and I get where the President's coming,
he was proven right on
that demands to the Fed
when he did because they did go too far--
- That's exactly right!
- But having said that, does he recognize
how weird it sounds to
love a robust economy
and a strong jobs report and
still advocate for lower rates?
It's like an oxymoron.
- No, it isn't.
We think the economy can grow even faster.
I mean the economy, probably
in the second quarter,
we're only gonna get about 2% growth.
The economy should be
growing at three to four,
by the way, if he gets that
trade deal done with China
and he gets the rate cut from
the Fed that we want in July,
if you think the economy's strong now,
wait until that happens.
So we just have a different model in mind.
We think the capacity of the U.S. economy
to grow faster, for
more jobs to be created,
more people in the
workforce is a lot faster.
I mean, remember, Larry
Summers who was Bill Clinton
and Barack Obama's economist,
before the election said,
"The top-most growth we can
get in this country is 2%."
remember that second year stagnation--
- [Neil] No, you're absolutely right,
you're absolutely right.
- And we're saying,
no, we're throwin' that model out!
We gonna grow this economy faster,
it's gonna have a very positive effect.
By the way, low inflation,
low unemployment
and how 'bout that, 50%
increase in the stock market,
that's $10 trillion of new wealth!
- Since he was elected, that's very true.
- There ya go.
- All right, Steve Moore,
great wisdom for a 39-year-old
man, I appreciate that.
(Steve laughs)
Have a great weekend, my friend.
- Have a great weekend.
You, too.
- Steve Moore.
All right, a lot more coming up after this
and then ask this question,
millennials leaving cities
so financially tight
that they can't make it
in the big city.
What is that saying?
After this.
- [Man] With my Hepatitis
C, I felt I couldn't be
at my best for my family.
In only eight weeks with
MAVYRET, I was cured
and left those doubts behind.
- [Female] I faced reminders
of my Hep C every day,
but in only eight weeks
with MAVYRET, I was cured.
- [Man] Even hanging with
friends, I worried about my Hep C,
but in only eight weeks
with MAVYRET, I was cured.
- [Announcer] MAVYRET is
the only eight-week cure
for all common types of Hep C.
Before starting MAVYRET
your doctor will test
if you've had Hepatitis
B, which may flare up
and cause serious liver problems
during and after treatment.
Tell you doctor if you've had Hepatitis B,
a liver or kidney transplant,
other liver problems,
HIV-1, or other medical conditions
and all medicines you take,
including herbal supplements.
Don't take MAVYRET with
atazanavir or rifampin,
or if you've had certain liver problems.
Common side effects include
headache and tiredness.
- With Hep C behind me, I feel free.
- Fearless.
- And there's no looking
back because I am cured.
- [Announcer] Talk to
your doctor about MAVYRET.
- [Announcer] The China threat.
- They want to be a global
superpower at our expense--
- [Announcer] So what's
America's next move
to keep the country in check?
Josh Hawley reacts on
"The Next Revolution".
(uplifting music)
- [Narrator] For those who
gaze up at starry skies
and ponder the vastness before them,
asking why,
where
and how,
this is CuriosityStream,
where you can stream
incredible documentaries
from the best filmmakers
anywhere in the world.
Long live the curious.
(pollen thumps)
(wind whooshes)
- Are you looking for a
trustworthy publishing company
to publish your book?
- Covenant Books is an
author-friendly publisher
who shares your passion and beliefs.
Call us today and we'll send
you a free author packet
to help get you started.
- [Announcer] Call 800-678-3402.
- [Announcer] I bet you've
never seen a bed like this!
It's the new Craftmatic
Legacy Rising Pillow Rest
Adjustable Bed, featuring
bed-side power plugs,
under-bed night lights and more.
For less, up to 50% less than
Tempur-Pedic, Sleep Number
and other adjustables.
Call now, you gotta see
how little they cost!
- Mom was diagnosed with
Alzheimer's at 58 years old.
- [Woman] This disease
just ravages a family.
- It changes your life.
If we work together, we
can stop this epidemic.
Now is the moment.
- [Woman] Contact
BrightFocus and learn more.
- [Announcer] Names matter,
your name, the name
you've made for yourself
and the name of the company you represent.
That's why at 4imprint, every name
and logo is printed with certainty.
Right the first time, on time, every time,
at a great price, guaranteed.
Because when you have passion,
integrity and certainty,
the only name they'll remember is yours.
Explore thousands of promotional
products at 4imprint.com.
4imprint, for certain.
- No, wrong move!
Old-fashioned bandages get dirty,
they can let in water and germs!
Look, it's falling off!
New-Skin is the flexible, liquid bandage
that seals out the bad stuff.
There's a spray, too!
- [Announcer] New-Skin,
rethink how you heal.
- They're young and restless
and now fleeing the big cities.
In a new report of the
Wall Street Journal,
it shows millennials are
getting out of the big cities
to escape the rising cost of living.
So is cheaper housing worth the switch
to the subs, or suburbs?
Back with us now is Erin
Gibbs, Jonas Max Ferris,
Deirdre Bolton, city residents all.
(laughs) I don't even
know if that's the case.
Erin, what do ya think of this?
- Well, I think this'll be
good for logistic companies
because they're gonna order
everything from Amazon still,
so I think that'll be
my stock market play.
It's gonna be great for FedEx--
- I love that about you,
you just find a way,
how can I profit off
this disturbing trend?
Jonas, what do you think?
- Is that where the
parents' basements are?
Is that why they're--
- They've moved up to the attic.
- I mean, look, I feel bad for millennials
because these cities, their
wealth is increasing faster
than their salaries.
They're entry-level workers in many cases
and they don't make enough to
keep up with the rising rents
because all the tech workers
and finance workers can pay higher rents.
So it's a tough situation,
but I don't think they're
being creative enough.
I do hear some stories about
$1,200 pods they're moving into
and like more unique things,
living in vans and boats
and they need to get creative.
You can't just run from the city,
that's where the income and the jobs are
and they're gonna try to save money
and be commuting three hours a day,
which isn't a good solution either.
- In fairness, the income
inequality really is growing.
I mean, we're sort of at a period in time
that I think hasn't been the
same since the late 1920s,
so I actually feel bad for
this group of kids, too.
Most of them do have student debt
and we know, outside of mortgage debt,
this is actually the biggest chunk
that Americans are carrying.
So there are a lot of factors
and I think you're right,
it's still expensive to live in cities,
which is why sometimes--
- I wonder whether they take
that frustration out at the polls,
if it's palpable to the
degree you say it is, right?
- Well, I think that is part
of Senator Sanders appeal
or other leftist candidates,
especially that student debt forgiveness.
I mean if you ignore how
(laughs) we're gonna pay for it,
or any of the logistics behind that--
- [Neil] Tax Jonas.
- I think that message
resonates for a reason.
- I think it's a matter
of whether they show up
to the polls, though,
'cause we do see consistently
low rates in actually voting.
So they may have a very large voice,
but whether that actually carries forward
to the votes is a whole 'nother story.
- Do you think their frustrations
are justifiable, though,
that they're really going
through something here
that we, as a nation,
have to pay attention to?
If they're leaving the
city to this degree.
- I'm not clear, I haven't decided yet.
I haven't seen a big
enough economic shift,
at least in the markets,
where we don't see them not spending.
They're still buying the
iPhones, they're still--
- And I see a lot of young
people here in the city--
- Yes, so I'm still saying
we're still seeing the consumer spending,
so maybe I think it maybe
it's more of a value shift.
I don't see that consumer spending is
suddenly dropping off from millennials,
they still contribute an
enormous amount to the economy.
So I think it's a matter
of value where they don't--
- Well they buy all,
the streaming services, right?
- Wanna pay for rent,
but they'll pay the streaming services.
So, from a Wall Street perspective,
I don't see them doing as poorly.
They're spending money.
- You know, it's funny, the
people that vote are the people
in the rent-controlled apartments
that aren't even working
anymore or they're retired.
These are apartments they
moved in the '60s in New York,
they're paying $200 a month
rent, hogging up space
that people--
- Makes me cry, yeah.
- Who work have to commute two hours.
So it's actually a failed liberal policy
that has driven millennials out--
- But that's kind of
a New York phenomenon,
not exclusively, right?
- San Francisco, you would
think it's an old '60s relic,
but I believe in Portland, Oregon
they just added rent control,
like that's a solution to this.
That only increases the problem
later, but it takes a while
and it seems like a thing people vote for.
- But in those hot cities,
especially for tech,
I saw something online and it was a shack
you would not leave a dog in,
and it was on a 1/4 of an
acre and it was $1.5 million,
but because it was in San Francisco.
So I do think it's hard
for millennials to come up
with $200,000 to put down as
a down payment in a house,
or an apartment in New
York City, San Francisco,
obviously there are cheaper cities--
- But isn't this rising--
- Austin, Texas.
- Economic tide lifting all boats, or no?
- For the most part, it is.
In fact, we see that when
it comes to wage growth,
when it comes to unemployment,
particularly with minorities.
We've seen just a massive rise
and more so with some of the
hardest hit demographics,
minority women, minorities in general,
have had some of the greatest rises.
So I think overall,
we're doing really well
and millennials are just,
I think they're really
just shifting their values.
They don't wanna pay as
much money for the cities,
they don't wanna pay as much rent--
- [Neil] Yeah, they've been burnt--
- But they still buy $100,000 iPhones.
- But they've been burnt by the meltdown,
they remember what their
parents went through
and may be very cautious.
Guys, I wanna thank you very much
for comin' in on a very
hot, humid Saturday
in the middle of July.
By the way,
we have the EPA Administrator
Andrew Wheeler joining us
on "Your World" 4:00 p.m. Eastern time.
Also, on FOX Business, we're
looking at the same issues
we did here about why the
young are feeling restless
and what happens to them
and how this election
could shape their minds.
All of that comin' up
next week, FOX continues--
- Using Ebates, I've earned $756.28.
- I've made close to $2,000.
Ebates basically gets a commission
from the stores that you shop at
and then they share the
commission with you.
- Every store that you
shop at will be on Ebates.
- It's free, it's fun, it's
super simple and it's safe,
why wouldn't I use it?
- Sign up for Ebates, get
cash back, it's awesome.
- [Announcer] Sign up for free,
shop at your favorite stores, get paid.
Join today and get a
$10 bonus at ebates.com.
- [Announcer] Are you dermaplaning yet?
- Your skin is just so
much smoother and clearer
and makeup goes on perfectly.
- My skin looks younger and healthier.
- My skin is instantly
brighter, it's amazing.
- [Announcer] Now you can bring
professional-style
dermaplaning into your home
with Flawless DermaPlane Glo,
the new exfoliating device
from Finishing Touch
that instantly transforms
your skin to a more radiant,
younger-looking complexion in minutes.
Flawless DermaPlane Glo instantly
and painlessly removes the
top layer of dry, dead skin
to reveal brighter, smoother,
younger-looking skin the
very first time you use it.
- Dermaplaning is the
most popular treatment
that my clients request.
The moment they get it, they are hooked,
you just can't get enough.
I love the DermaPlane Glo,
it's very user friendly,
it gives like a really
radiant, dewy-glow to the skin.
- I can't stop touching my face!
- [Announcer] An
easy-to-use contour design,
a professional-grade exfoliating
edge with safety guard
and just like a professional treatment,
a built-in LED light so
you never miss a spot.
- It's very easy to do.
- [Announcer] It's gentle
on all skin types and tones.
Your makeup will never look flawless
if it's sitting on top of
dead skin and peach fuzz,
but DermaPlane Glo exfoliates that layer
to create a smooth surface
for creams and makeup.
- My makeup just glides on,
even my moisturizer,
my skin care products,
they go on easier.
- The DermaPlane Glo transforms my skin
from dull to radiant and glowing.
It gets rid of all the dead skin cells,
all of the peach fuzz
and basically gives you brand-new skin.
- [Announcer] Get your
Flawless DermaPlane Glo,
including exfoliating
heads for easy replacement.
Go online now at
dermaplaneglo.com for only $19.99,
with a 60-day money-back guarantee.
Or call 1-800-419-6401.
Order right now and your shipping is free!
- It's unbelievable,
I'm glowing right now.
- [Announcer] Flawless DermaPlane Glo,
brighter, more youthful-looking
skin instantly.
- When I book at hilton.com,
I get to select my room
from the floor plan,
free Wi-Fi and the price match guarantee.
- So with Hilton there is no catch.
- (laughs) Yeah, the only
catch is I'm never leaving.
(woman laughs)
No, I'm serious, I live here now.
Book at hilton.com and get the
Hilton Price Match Guarantee.
(dramatic percussion music)