- Darden Restaurants, I think that
that one is a good one right now.
I think they're going to
continue to raise and beat
in the restaurant sector
per my Analyst Lin Collier
at Luke Capital, we're going with it.
- [Scott] All right Kate Moore,
always good to have you here.
- Yeah, consumers what I'm watching
the most next week during earnings.
I think we're going to get
a lot of different reads
about the staples and
the discretionary side
with unemployment at
multi-decade lows, wages growing.
I think this is the big thing
that can change sentiment.
- [Scott] Okay, Weis,
quick, what do you got?
- [Weis] Illumina.
- [Scott] Josh Brown?
- [Josh] I'm going with Twitter.
- Motorola Solutions MSI.
- All right, good stuff.
Thanks everybody.
Good weekend, good holiday as well.
The Exchange starts now.
(upbeat music)
- And thank you Scott.
Hi everybody, I am Brian
Sullivan in for Kelly Evans today
and here's what's ahead:
D.C. and Your Money.
Politicians in America
will debate the meaning of
the Mueller Report, but we
ask could it lead to even more
gridlock and standstill in D.C.?
We're going to review the
impact on your money ahead.
Pinning and conferencing,
Zoom and Pinterest
hitting the market to a
lot of investor fanfare,
but could they suffer
ultimately the same fate
as Lyft shareholders?
Plus, a fold fail, a
cannabis consolidation,
a recyclable shoe, you heard that right,
and a new legal smoking age.
That's what's ahead in Rapid Fire.
It's a big league show with lots to do,
but as we always do let's
start with Your Money.
Dom Chu is here now with
a DOW that is up, what?
- Almost 100 points and stable right now
for the most part Sulli.
If you take a look at the markets overall,
nixed only because the
NASDAQ is lagging off
by about 1/10th of 1%.
Still though, the S&P
up by about three points
and the DOW Industrials just
about 100 points to the upside.
That's pretty decent overall,
we'll see if that sticks.
One particular industry group to focus on,
the transportation stocks.
The iShares Dow Jones Transportation ETF,
which tracks the Dow Transports,
right now the highest
levels that we've seen
going all the way back to December third,
so Transport's a big part of that story.
Union Pacific earnings
better than expected,
that's driving the trade there
and if you're looking for
one of the stocks of the day
that's not Zoom, that's not Pinterest,
check out Blackstone.
Look at this, 8.5% gains.
A publicly traded partnership
for private equity
that's going to become a
publicly traded corporation,
that new structure giving
a boost to those shares.
A lot more investors could come in the mix
and they raised a lot of money, Brian,
for their funds last
year, back over to you.
- Yeah, Schwartz been on Squawk Box
talking that up this morning.
Dom Chiu will see you in it
a bit, thank you very much.
All right so and the markets that Dom
just walked you through
have two new members
to welcome into the fold today.
Of course you've heard the names,
Pinterest and Zoom both are
now public, both rising.
Just adding to the list of names,
including some very under-the-radar ones.
that have done very well
when they hit the tape.
Bob Pisani is at the New
York Stock Exchange with more
and Bob, Zoom, what a day.
- Both of them.
I mean not only, the floodgates
have really opened Brian,
not only did they raise
the terms going into it
but they popped at the open as well.
Let's just take a look here.
Pinterest, very simple.
Price talk was 15 to
17, they priced it at 19
but wait a minute, it opened at $23.75
and take a look at it in
intraday trading here,
on very heavy volume here,
they're gonna trade the whole float today.
It's holding up very well, up $24.35.
Zoom though, 28 to 32.
Just four or five days
ago we were talking about
28 to 32 for Zoom.
It priced at 36, that's not a typo.
It opened at $65.
This is very rare to see something
that essentially opens twice as high
as anybody thought it would a week ago
and you see a trading right here at $63,
just off that number.
Of course it's profitable,
A lot of people like that.
It's got 100% growth and
those are the two magic words
that we've got.
Recent IPOs that joins the parade,
they've done really well.
Jumia, PagerDuty, Tufin, Levi Strauss,
which is one of the few
profitable companies,
all doing great.
Lyft is one of the few
companies still to the downside.
No companies next week Brian
but the week after we'll
probably get another slew,
maybe iHeartMedia, maybe next
Friday a week from tomorrow,
maybe we'll get Uber giving us some terms.
We'll see, not quite sure yet about that.
- Big stuff there Bob
Pisani, thank you very much.
All right now to Washington
because the other big
thing to hit the tape today
was the Mueller Report.
It is perhaps more heavily
redacted than many had thought
or hoped, but at 400 or so pages long
our team is still pouring through it.
Eamon Javers live at the White House
with what we have learned so far.
Eamon, your key takeaways.
- Yeah, Brian that's right.
We are still trying to
digest this 400 page report
and going through it for
all of the details here.
The headline is out there
and the President's been
saying that throughout the day,
no collusion, no obstruction.
That's good news for this White House.
Inside the document we're finding
some of the areas of
concern for Robert Mueller
particularly around the area
of potential obstruction
of justice and the
President's public statements,
his tweets even about some of the people
involved in this whole situation,
those were red flags from Robert Mueller
in certain circumstances.
Particularly on this idea.
- All right so when we get Eamon back up,
we're gonna come back
and talk more about that
certainly here.
Somebody pulled the plug
literally on Eamon there as well,
but luck we've got a couple smart folks
surrounding us right now
to dig more into this.
Let's talk more about what
this all means for Washington,
the markets, and policy going forward.
We're gonna CNBC this story.
Let's bring in Libby Cantrell
Head of Public Policy
at PIMCO.
CNBC's own Ron Insana
and John Harwood as well.
Libby, I'll begin with you.
The Democrats are gonna complain,
it's too heavily redacted.
We need to investigate further.
Republicans will say this is all over.
What we're probably going to
end up with is a bunch of this.
Where do you see policy
making, infrastructure,
anything else, going forward?
- Yeah, I mean I think
this is hitting through
a partisan lens.
I mean to your point
Republicans are sort of
claiming vindication here,
that there is no collusion,
and Democrats may walk through the door
that the Mueller report opened in terms of
investigating further,
whether there is actually
obstruction of justice.
I think you'll hear louder calls
for even then maybe the
beginnings of impeachment hearings
for the President among
the progressive left.
Now I think Speaker
Pelosi will do everything
that she can to try to
not heed those calls,
but the point is that look,
I mean Washington has already
been, is already polarized.
It is already partisan.
There was not much moving
legislatively anyway,
but the big things that President Trump
does want to move legislatively,
one is is the NAFTA replacement,
the USMCA, NAFTA 2.0.
And that might be harder to move now
with a more kind of
fractured relationship--
- Do you believe that Ron,
to Libby's point that this
report will in some ways
infect what should be
bipartisan or nonpartisan
purely economic negotiations?
- Yeah, I don't think there's any escaping
maybe the overhang that Libby alluded to,
which is that within the
obstruction of justice component
of this report Bob Mueller
effectively punted to Congress
and suggested in the
absence of his being able
to do anything under the
Office of Legal Counsel,
which says you cannot
indict a sitting President.
He really suggested that
Congress, to a certain extent,
take this up.
So to the extent that
they're not only one,
maybe distracted or even obsessed by this,
it will slow down the legislative process
and create even more I think fractures
between the Democrats in the House
and the White House itself.
- You know John when
Barr's letter came out,
the four pager, people
said okay this is over.
It appears to what Ron
is maybe suggesting that
maybe we are just getting started
on a second phase of this.
- Well I think that's
because Barr's letter
was such a brief summary of
this and the report today
gives us a lot more
detail as Eamon was saying
before somebody pulled the plug,
that a lot of detail about
the potential obstruction
that the President had engaged in
orders to Don McGahn then
the White House Counsel
to direct Rod Rosenstein
to fire Robert Mueller.
The special counsel began
refusing offering his resignation
then ultimately staying on a while longer
and telling aides that Trump had asked him
to do crazy stuff.
I think all of that and
to Libby's point earlier,
I think it was the right one.
I believe that the way the
administration through Bill Barr
in the initial release of the letter
and then today's press conference
in which he seemed to be
spinning for the President
trying to blunt the impact of the report,
I think that's going to
make it more difficult
for Speaker Pelosi to
resist those in her caucus
who insist on an impeachment
proceeding to weigh this
in a way that they think
is searching and fair.
- Yeah, and Eamon Javers by
the way is alive and well.
(laughing)
I just want to point that out he is back.
Somebody pulled the plug,
but not on him literally.
So Eamon--
- There's no censorship here.
- No censorship here, he
is back with us as well.
- He's not redacted.
- You know you've been
there day in and day out
for us Eamon.
You've seen the sort of the
back and the forth inside.
You know the Speaker's
chamber and talking about this
with Sarah Sanders and and one wonders
how much more of any dialogue that we have
is simply going to be about
the report from now on?
The administration can want
to talk about defense spending
or infrastructure or
immigration or whatever it is
and every question is going
to go back to this report
with the exception of maybe yours.
- Well, you know that's right.
I mean first of all this is a White House
that doesn't brief the
press any more, right?
So they're not going to face
this public televised spectacle
of the White House trying to
get out its line of the day
and reporters just asking them
on camera about the report.
You're gonna see the
President leaving here
shortly this afternoon a couple of hours
and reporters will ask him questions.
I expect he will talk.
He's been tweeting vigorously today.
He has a lot he wants to say about this,
so I expect we're gonna
get lengthy comments
from the President today.
But in talking to some
of the officials here,
I don't get the sense that
they're gonna rebut much
of this at all.
It's possible that they're
just gonna let this sit
and retreat to the headline
conclusion of no collusion,
no obstruction and on
some of the smaller things
just let all those go.
For example, there's some stuff
in here about Sarah Sanders
and exactly how she
responded to the Comey firing
by suggesting that FBI
agents inside the bureau
had lost confidence in Comey
and that they'd heard from
countless members of the FBI
who said that they didn't like Comey.
Apparently in her interview
with the special counsels team,
she admitted that you know
that didn't have any basis
in fact and it was either
a slip of the tongue
or she just kind of said it at the time
and didn't really base it
on any actual factual basis.
Those smaller things it doesn't seem like
the White House is
going to address at all.
They might just let them all go.
They're content with the win here
and they feel like they've had
a big positive political day.
- Yeah and Brian I'm not sure
how much of a win there is.
I mean I got through about the
first 50 pages of the report
and there's some even
materiality when it comes to
the question of whether
or not the administration
or I should say the
campaign expected to benefit
from Russia's actions in interfering.
Not rising to the level of criminality,
which Robert Mueller suggested,
but from a market perspective
this may as Amy just alluded,
in many ways turn neutral insofar as
we're seeing a
resynchronization of let's say
Chinese and American economic growth.
Europe's the outlier at the moment.
We're seeing the Fed back off,
we're seeing central
banks around the world
start to stimulate.
So if indeed today's retail sales number
were any indication of
where we're going from here
then the market may just
return it's attention
to fundamentals and maybe ignore some--
- Ron, dang you for bringing
right back down the CNBC lane
because that was perfect and
I want to talk about that.
It's amazing, the retail sales
number better than expected.
Jobless claims under 200000.
GDP revisions, they are
going up at Goldman Sachs
and others today Libby.
It's amazing that this is
getting all the headlines
and if you just focused
on this you'd think
this is the only thing
happening but outside of this
America rolls on and the economy rolls on
and the President will
have a strong economy
most likely behind him in that reelection.
- Yeah, most likely and our view of him,
is that we likely will see sort of two,
2.5% growth here in the
United States for 2019.
You do have the effect
of fading fiscal stimulus
and you got a big fiscal
impulse growth from the tax bill
that was passed in at late 2017
and then also a big
government spending bill
that was passed in 2018.
From a policy perspective
and from kind of tying
this back to markets,
another area though of
this kind of Mueller report
that could inform relations with Congress,
that could be relevant, is this idea of
the fiscal cliff of 2020.
And the markets are not
focused on this right now,
this is something we're
talking about with per clients
and talking at PIMCO go
about and that's because
if Congress doesn't step
it and keep spending levels
at the rate that they are now,
come January 1st of 2020 we
could see a half a percent
headwind to economic growth
because of this big drive down
in spending now.
I think we all, Washington
folks are you know,
understand that Congress is expedient.
They're going to want not want
to do that going into it--
- Well they may want to do that.
- John Harwood, John Harwood.
- Brian, I just wanted to make one point,
which is that in terms of the effect
on the legislative agenda,
there really isn't much
of a legislative agenda.
In theory the administration
wants an infrastructure plan,
but Republican leaders in Congress don't
and the kind of plan the
administration wants is not
what Democrats want so
other than the USMCA,
which is significant,
there isn't much that congress might do
in the absence of this Mueller report
so I think that's important and--
- John, let me ask you, let
me ask you Libby's point
if I can because we're
running out of time.
Do you, to the fiscal cliff discussions,
do you believe it's not
only because the report
but maybe the report layers on,
that the US Congress,
Democrats and Republicans both,
will play economic chicken
with the fiscal cliff
and the US economy?
- I doubt it.
I don't think Democrats
approach these issues
differently from Republicans
and while they'll fight for
their policy priorities,
I don't think that a
Nancy Pelosi led House
would engage in the degree of brinkmanship
that we've seen in the recent past.
- Let's hope.
535 men and women fighting
while 310 million others may suffer.
John Thank You, Eamon thank you,
I'm glad to see you're alive and well.
Ron Insana, Libby Cantrill,
thank you all very much.
All right we are just getting
started here on The Exchange.
Here's what else is coming up.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Ahead, the
CEO of BB&T joins us.
We'll talk earnings, the
progress on its big merger,
and the outlook for the economy.
IPO Bonanza.
Investors pinned their hopes on Pinterest
and Zoom zooms higher.
Should you get in?
And could 21 soon be the new
18 when it comes to tobacco?
We'll explain.
This is The Exchange on CNBC.
♪ I want it all ♪
♪ And I want it now ♪
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] With the
Grubhub delivery app,
(whistling)
if you want it all, you can get it all.
Grubhub, restaurants you love, delivered.
- [Girl] I love my grandma.
- [Announcer] As you grow
older your brain naturally
begins to change, which may
cause trouble with recall.
- [Boy] Learning from him is great,
when I can keep up.
- [Announcer] Thankfully
Prevagen helps your brain
and improves memory.
- [Man] Dad's got all the answers.
- [Announcer] Prevagen is
now the number one selling
brain health supplement
in drugstores nationwide.
- [Girl] She outsmarts
meet every single time.
- Checkmate.
You want to play again?
- [Announcer] Prevagen,
healthier brain, better life.
- [Announcer] You work hard
and operate at the speed of humanity.
CNBC on Xfinity X1 puts
your future in your hands.
Delivering real-time information
whenever you want it.
- We always try different
ways to show people the data.
- [Announcer] With real world
perspective wherever you are.
I think the housing
prices have to come down.
They're too expensive.
- [Announcer] CNBC, anywhere,
anytime, on any screen
with Xfinity X1 and on the
go with the Xfinity stream.
- If you bought a
timeshare for your family
by now you've learned the ugly truth.
Timeshares are the only
thing that you can buy
that you don't know how
much it's going to cost
or when it's going to end.
It's like giving them a blank
check for annual maintenance
and assessment fees.
Sounds crazy, right?
The ugly truth is that this never ends.
Even when you die your family
will be stuck with this burden.
Hello, I'm Chuck McDowell and 10 years ago
I founded Wesley Financial
Group with one goal in mind,
helping good folks just like you
cancel their timeshare contract.
And what that means for
you and your family:
no more mortgage payments,
no more maintenance fees surprises,
and no more timeshare.
So call today, the call is free.
The information kit is free
and I guarantee if we can't
cancel your timeshare contract,
you'll pay nothing.
- [Announcer] You can legally
get out of your timeshare.
For your free information
kit explaining how,
call 800-395-8811, 800-395-8811.
(upbeat music)
- Hi, welcome back.
With so much talk about the possibility
of an economic slowdown
it's important to look
beyond just the government data.
Jim Cramer told you as much
on Mad Money the other night.
So let's do more of that by diving into
BB&T's latest quarter.
Joining us exclusively on
The Exchange is Kelly King,
the Chairman and CEO of BB&T.
Kelly it's great to
have you on the program.
So much discussion about a
possibility of a slowdown.
How is BB&T seeing loan demand?
- Well glad to be back.
Long demand is actually very good.
Actually production is very high.
Our pipeline where we kind of measure
all of the applications in process
are at an all-time high
and so we're seeing a
broad-based level of confidence,
a broad-based level of
willingness to borrow money,
to invest in plant and capital equipment.
So overall it's very good.
You know on the street doesn't match up
with a lot of the kind of
national rhetoric that you hear.
- And in your experience,
your long history Kelly running a bank,
do people borrow money,
do businesses borrow money
when they sense a slowdown is imminent?
- They do.
Brian, it's interesting.
- They do?!
- Yeah, they do.
I travel around and I talked
to lots of business people
one on one and so when I talked to them
they talk about their business.
They're interested in chatting
about the national issues
but when you get right down
to what they're going to do,
they focus on their business.
So if their actual market,
if their actual business is slowing down
then of course they'll
reduce their investment.
But if it's just a lot
of general conversation,
you know they'll talk about it,
it might cause them some uneasiness,
but when they go right back to the office
they'll focus on running their business.
- From all the numbers
though in the quarter
and the year so far
Kelly that you have seen
do you believe we will be in a
recession in 12 to 18 months?
- You know, I actually do not.
I'd be honest six or eight nine months ago
I was a lot more concerned
about the possibility of that.
There was just so much rhetoric
about it's been 10 years
and after a while everybody
begins to you know,
have that effect you a bit.
But as I've gotten out and traveled around
and talked to business people
and I've seen the strength.
I mean just what you've been reporting
just in the last hour so.
Strong retail sales, low
unemployment, low jobless claims,
underlying strong GDP, no
major geopolitical risk,
it seemed to be eminently problematic.
I don't see, in certainly
the next 12 to 18 months
I do not see and eminent slowdown.
I think that you could have
some existential factors
that could cause that but I don't think
it's predictable at this time.
- One thing that stood out to me
that was a little bit
shocking I guess Kelly,
is that your net interest margin, NIM,
rose only two bits. (laughs)
Literally a tiny percent.
- We take what we can get.
- I know but it rose even
as interest rates collapsed
in the first quarter, how did that happen?
- Well we have a very,
very strong what we call
core deposit funding structure.
We're like a really big community bank.
We operate a regional bank structure.
We're in a lot of rural areas.
We're in metro urban areas as well,
but we have a lot of stable deposits.
They're not as price sensitive,
they're more focused on relationships.
A lot of small business clients
and so our NIM pressure
is more a function of
what's happening in our local markets
than it is in the national markets.
So when you hear a lot of
national discussion about
changes in NIM, it doesn't
inherently affect us.
Now sometimes if we do some external large
and negotiable instrument funding
that'll move our NIM around a little bit.
But in this particular
quarter what we really saw was
that our funding was increasing
but our rate of return
on assets was increasing
at a faster rate.
- You know one quick last question.
You're paying an advertising
agency a lot of money
to come up with a new brand
between SunTrust and BB&T
when you merge.
Can you give us some kind of a of a hint
as to what that's shaping up to be?
Because SunTrust and
BB&T could mosh together
like some kind of kids
drink if you're not careful.
- Yeah.
Well you know Brian, the reason we decided
to pick a new name versus
using either one of the others
or some combination is because our merger
is about improving profitability,
which it does enormously.
But it's much more importantly
about leaning forward
about major investments and
innovation and technology.
It's about really getting excited about
meeting the needs of the
clients in terms of technology
and trust, kind of that
blended relationship
between technology and the branches.
And so we want a name that
kind of a points forward
that excites our clients,
excites our associates,
and excites the market in general to say
this is an institution
that is moving forward,
is energized and trying to
take care of the community
at large and the clients in particular,
and we think we can find such a name.
- Good luck.
You're a bank, Kelley
King we do wish you luck.
Appreciate that, have a
good Easter, thank you.
- Thank you, you too.
- All right, on deck,
the trade war comes home.
How China and Wisconsin are now in a fight
and it's over with some say
our Foxconn's broken promises.
But first, to the moon Zoom.
Both stocks trading but
one is really taking off,
but do we need to learn
from Lyft that one day
does not an investment make.
We dig into Zoom and
Pinterest a little more
when we're back.
(upbeat music)
(electronic music)
- Introducing Nutrisystem spring sale.
Save 50%, yes 50%.
- [Announcer] Lose up to
13 pounds and seven inches
in your first month.
- I'm Marie and I lost 50
pounds with Nutrisystem.
- I lost 60 pounds with Nutrisystem.
- There's even a money-back guarantee.
- [Announcer] Order your
28-day plan right now.
Save 50% off every program.
- Call or go online right now.
- [Announcer] Go online
or call 877-983-FIT4
right now to say 50% plus
get probiotic shakes free.
(piano music)
- If you spent years
building your investments
on mutual funds it may
be time to graduate.
If you have more than a
half a million dollars
in investible assets, there's
almost always better options
and mutual funds that
improve tax efficiency,
are cheaper and more
specifically customizable.
Mutual funds are a perfectly fine way
for beginning investors,
but Fisher Investments can give you ideas
to help you for who you are now.
- [Announcer] Call now
for your free report
Five Pitfalls of Mutual Funds
with insights from best-selling author
and legendary money manager Ken Fisher.
Call now 1-800-972-4411.
- At Fisher Investments we
help you with the process
of graduating to a better future.
- [Announcer] Call for your free report
Five Pitfalls of Mutual Funds.
You'll learn about their disadvantages
and why it may be time for a new approach.
Call now: 1-800-972-4411.
- You can achieve your investment goals
and Fisher Investments
can help you get there.
(audience applauding)
- Who says our bank isn't tech enough?
(audience booing)
Everybody look at your phones.
The design thinking, digital engineering,
security, block chain, and
we will be first to market!
(audience applauding)
Yes.
- When do we launch?
- Unfortunately in two or three...
Hours.
(audience applauding)
- [Man] Why the delay?
- [Announcer] Cognizant is helping banks
use digital technologies at scale
to advance speed to market.
(upbeat music)
- All right, welcome back.
Pinterest and Zoom may be getting
all the headline love today
but they are not the only names
that you need to know about.
Here are some of the
other movers at the hour.
Sketchers, a shoemakers
sinking after missing earnings
and sales estimates.
Second quarter profit guidance
was also below forecast.
That stock is down.
On the flip side Honeywell, it's up.
They posted strong results
and they also raised
their full year forecast.
Companies saying it saw strong demand
for its aerospace products.
And Travelers is taking
a journey higher today,
leading the DOW.
The insurance company
beating EPS estimates
but it did miss a bit on revenues.
Travelers though also
did raise its dividend
and that stock is higher.
All right now let's get to Contessa brewer
with a CNBC news update, Contessa.
- Hi there Brian.
Here's what's happening right now.
Democrats vying for the party's
2020 Presidential nomination
including New York
senator Kirsten Gillibrand
are condemning Attorney
General William Barr
for acting like a defender
of President Trump.
She had some harsh words
about Barrs' news conference this morning.
- The Attorney General
of the United States
is supposed to represent the
people of the United States.
He's not supposed to
represent President Trump.
And by having this press conference today
that is misleading the American
people was not appropriate.
- A French judicial police official
says investigators think
an electrical short-circuit
most likely caused Notre
Dame's Cathedral fire.
He says the investigators still don't have
the green light to work in the cathedral
because of safety concerns.
Rescue services use two
cranes to pull out a bus,
which crashed on
Portugal's Madeira Island.
Killed 29 German tourists
and injured 28 people.
The bus was lying on its side
was part of its roof torn off.
That's your CNBC news update this hour.
Brian, send it back to you.
- All right Contessa, thank you very much.
Well a pair of Technology unicorns,
billion dollars of the
public market are surging
after their public debuts today.
Pinterest pricing above
the high end of the range
at $19 a share and opened up 25%.
That sounds good until you hear this.
Zoom video communications, the ticker ZM,
priced at $36 a share
but only opened up 80%.
Lets those talk about both
and start with Pinterest.
CEO Ben Silbermann telling Squawk Alley
the company is more
about utility for people
to get things done and
less of a place to talk
or for friends or to follow celebrities.
In other words, we are not
a social media company.
For more let's bring in Doug
Clinton Managing Director
at Loop Ventures as well
as our own Leslie Picker.
Amazing response to Pinterest.
Are you surprised?
A 25% pop.
Either the bankers
screwed up in pricing it
or people really liked Pinterest.
- People do like it and to your point,
it's a discovery platform.
It's really not a social network
although we think it will be
comped like a social network.
So I think the good
thing about Pinterest is
it's a great business.
They have this unique data
asset where people tell
Pinterest how they see
the world in pictures,
how they categorize the world.
The problem is companies like
Facebook, Twitter, Snapchat,
the companies that will
be comped on Pinterest
are trading six to eight
times next year's revenue.
Pinterest at this valuation
is closer to 11 times.
So it feels like the market
is already pricing in
a lot of that great business.
- I mean first off, I
think the term social media
is outdated and dumb.
I mean let's just be honest.
It's just media at this point.
That said, do you think
there was a strategic reason
why the CEO of Pinterest kept saying
we're not social media,
because he didn't kind of want that stain.
- Yeah, I think social media
is a bad word right now.
I mean you look at what's happening
with Facebook and Twitter.
- It's two words John.
- Two bad words combined into one.
I think you look at Facebook and Twitter
and sort of what's happened with them
and public sentiment around,
especially privacy on Facebook,
but also the the conversation
just politically.
The discourse is very
difficult on both platforms.
Pinterest talks a lot in there S1 about
empowering their users.
I think that's a very different message
than what we're seeing
Facebook and Twitter do
with their users where you
have FOMO and depression.
- You know what's amazing Leslie Picker?
Besides you by the way, is
that if a stock falls 25%
everyone screams Wall Street
really screwed that up.
If a stock rises 25%,
nobody's saying anything.
It's still obviously 25% mispriced.
You see where I'm going with this?
- Yeah, it's tough to
price an IPO perfectly
and if it closed flat today
people would complain about that too.
But in terms of Pinterest,
this company sold primary shares only
which means that all of the
money raised from the IPO
went back into the coffers of the company.
There were no selling shareholders
that were raising money
to fund their own pockets.
So what that means essentially
is if you do see a 25% pop,
that is a loss of capital,
that is money left on the table
that Pinterest could have otherwise used
to reinvest in their business.
Now that said, it is important
to keep investors happy
with these IPOs.
You want investors who are
kind of gonna stick around
for the long run through that
six month lock-up period,
which expires in about 180 days.
You want people that can stick around
and the best way to make them happy
is to make the money Brian.
- Yeah, it certainly is.
All right let's move on now to Zoom Video
because if you thought
Pinterest was doing well
and by the way it is.
Nobody's taking anything
away from 25% gains.
Zoom, new ticker ZM, soaring.
Up more than 75%.
Let's bring in Deirdre
Bosa from San Francisco.
Deirdre, okay Zoom getting a lot of love,
but it also faces a lot of competition.
- That's right Brian and
I think Zoom's performance
says as much about the company as it does
about all the other big
enterprise tech names out there
who haven't been able to capitalize on
this video conferencing software.
You've got a very crowded field here.
You've got Microsoft,
which has been pushing Skype for Business.
Cisco's WebEx, which Eric
Yuan actually works for
and then Zoom seemingly
comes out of nowhere
and sort of takes this
field and is the leader
and known to be easier to use
and part of the reason for that is because
it started in the cloud.
Some of the other competitors
and big names in this space
started on antiquated
conference call or chat software
so that's been one of its big successes
and I think that also
speaks to the argument
and some of its risk factors.
How could it continue to compete against
these very well capitalized
big tech name competitors.
Eric Yuan has built a company
that was just more simple
and easier to use.
That's when it strengthened.
You can understand how
it may be continuing
to use these strengths to
expand into different verticals
like telehealth and education.
- All right Deirdre Bosa in San Francisco,
Leslie Picker in New York,
Doug Clinton here in Englewood Cliffs.
Guys, great discussion,
thank you very much.
Here's what's ahead on The Exchange.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Coming up
cannabis consolidation heats up.
Could big changes be coming
to the tobacco world?
Plus a recyclable sneaker and a fold fail.
It's all ahead in Rapid Fire.
- [Narrator] How well does your
financial adviser know you?
If they saw you on the
street would your adviser
recognize you?
At a Ameriprise we see
you as more than a client.
That's why our advisers care
about what's important to you.
They offer personalized
advice to help you prepare
for what's expected and even what's not.
Giving you the freedom to
live financially confident
because to us you're more
than just another face
in the crowd.
With the right financial
adviser life can be brilliant.
Ameriprise Financial.
- [Announcer] 10 seconds left.
- Pass.
- [Announcer] John Moore Ways to inbound.
- Yo, you check FanDuel lately?
I didn't know they had
a single-game fantasy.
- [Announcer] Sammy Win behind home plate.
One out to go.
- [Announcer] Moreways in win,
looking to make something here.
- A NASCAR contest.
Oh, golf.
- [Announcer] More ways throws.
- [Announcer] Win shoots.
- There's just--
- More ways to win!
- [Announcer] More ways to win!
- [Announcer] More ways to--
- Win!
- That's what I'm telling you.
There are more ways to with FanDuel.
♪ I want it all ♪
- Burgers.
Donuts.
Nicoise salad?
- [Announcer] Delivering from over
95000 restaurants nationwide.
♪ I want it all ♪
If you want it all.
You can get it all.
Gruhub, restaurants you love, delivered.
- [Announcer] We see home staying cooler
without the planet getting warmer.
At Emerson when issues become inspiration,
creating a better world
isn't just a result,
it's a responsibility.
Emerson, consider it's solved.
- [Announcer] Paid spokesperson.
- This is a legal alert for
users of Roundup Weed Killer.
Roundup Weed Killer has been designated
as a probable human carcinogen
by the World Health Organization
and in July 2018 a judge determined that
all federal law suits could
move forward against Monsanto,
the maker of Roundup Weed Killer,
over concerns that
those exposed to Roundup
are at risk for developing
non-hodgkin's lymphoma.
And in a landmark 289 million
dollar verdict in August 2018
a jury concluded that
Monsanto's Roundup Weed Killer
and Ranger Pro Herbicides contributed
to a school grounds keeper's
non-hodgkin's lymphoma.
Roundup Weed Killer is the
most commonly used weed killer
in American agriculture.
If you or someone you love
has been diagnosed with
non-hodgkin's lymphoma
after being exposed to Roundup
or glyphosate herbicide,
you may be entitled to compensation.
How do you fight for the
compensation you deserve?
You choose the right legal
team that has the experience,
support staff, and resources
to seek the most compensation
for your injuries.
Call now.
- [Announcer] Catch the Shark Tank
'Life Made Easy' Marathon.
Everything you need when you need it.
- I'm going to incorporate your
key into your mobile phone.
- [Announcer] The Shark Tank
'Life Made Easy' Marathon.
Starts tonight seven eastern.
CNBC, get yours.
Brought to you by Xfinity.
(upbeat music)
- All right, welcome back.
Let's catch you up on a few stories
that should be on your radar right now.
They call it rapid-fire
and here with their takes
we have Bill Griffith, Kate
Rodgers, Frank Holland.
Only one of you will emerge alive.
- Yes, I know.
Are we gonna get a word in
edgewise here, my friend?
- No, that's why it's gonna be good.
(laughing)
First off--
- Shots fired.
- We haven't even started.
- I want to survive.
- You're in, you win.
- Yes.
- All right, first up
Senator Mitch McConnell
announcing a bill that will
bump the national minimum age
to buy tobacco from 18 to 21.
It's just a bill, not of law yet.
It would also apply to vaping
products and we should note,
some states in America already
have a minimum age of 21
so this would be kind of a symbolic move
to four states to do it.
Frank Holland, it's
kind of your beat here.
What's the reaction, what do you think?
- Well listen, there's
also a similar House bill
called the Scott Act named after
outgoing FDA Chief Scott Gottlieb.
Here's the thing, a lot of
stats we can throw out here.
Here's just another one,
90% of current smokers
tried a cigarette by
the time they were 18.
This is really a public health initiative
and I think it makes perfect sense.
There's 16 million Americans
with a smoking related disease
in America right now and it's a problem.
- Let me play the cynic here.
This is the tobacco
industry trying to get out
in front of any regulations
that are going to
come their way.
Why now after Scott Gottlieb
had already gone after
the vaping companies because
there was a 75% increase
in the use of those by teens.
Now all of a sudden we have legislation
and surprise, surprise,
the tobacco companies
are supporting said legislation to raise
the minimum age to 21.
- It's amazing Bill, right?
After they have these pods for vaping
that are basically candy flavored.
- Exactly, yes.
- And JUUL the maker of many of those
is actually in support of
21 years to buy tobacco,
but I mean the McConnell release did have
some disturbing things
in it including that
middle schoolers we're
starting to vape as well.
We hear so much about teens
and kids in high school
doing this and I totally
agree with the marketing.
It does seem like candy and
you don't necessarily realize
there's nicotine in it.
It is not good for you.
- By the way, there's more nicotine in it
in many of these cases
than in regular cigarettes.
- All right, so it's bout
time they go to 21 anyway.
They should have done that years ago.
The drinking age is 21,
why not the smoking age?
- Well I understand you but a
lot of states, a lot of towns,
they've already raised it,
so I just think it makes a lot of sense
and two things can be
right at the same time.
It might be good for tobacco's
business somehow, some way,
but it's also good for public health.
- [Bill] Of course.
- Look I'm gonna ask you this Kate
because you are the youngest
one on this fine panel,
which is do you believe that raising the,
and I'm not asking you to
reveal any personal details
about high school but do you believe
that raising the age of something
does prevent people from doing it?
- I think if there's a will there's a way.
I was an angel in high
school and I am still today,
but I'm just saying.
- [Bill] You still are.
- But I think if kids want to
get their hands on something,
you know we can prevent it
by putting laws like this
in place but again, like I said,
when there's a will there's a way.
- Probably a kid named
Will selling JUUL pods
at the high school.
All right, topic number two.
Kind of related.
Cannabis consolidation.
Canadian weed giant Canopy Growth striking
a 4.3 billion dollar deal
to buy Acreage Holding.
That deal however will
take effect after cannabis
has been legalized in the US.
While legal cannabis sales
have been climbing this year
so far the black markets also been rising.
What's the future Bill of this industry?
- You know what I find
interesting about this deal,
this is almost like a
futures contract for Canopy.
What they're doing is locking
in a price for Acreage.
- [Brian] It's an option.
- But at the same time I wonder
why Acreage would do this
deal if they're locking themselves into,
it's a 43% premium over the
company's valuation right now,
but what's to say that they
couldn't see an even higher
valuation after we do inevitably see--
- So Bill Griffith you're saying
that this could be actually
a sign of lack of optimism
by Acreage Holdings.
- By Acreage Holdings, yes,
but Canopy I think is
making a very smart plan.
- Oh, that's what I was just gonna say.
Acreage is a multi-state operator.
It's in about 20 states already.
Obviously this is contingent on
federal nationwide legalization,
but really smart move for
Canopy and also Constellation,
which I know you have your eye on but--
- Yeah absolutely, great
move for Constellation.
Yeah, they have some
warrants where they can,
similar option, they can decide
to buy more stake in Canopy
but a lot of people are talking
about the cannabis play.
Me, I'm looking more
at the Acreage business
and the people they have on it's board.
They have Bill Weld a guy
who's running for President,
former Governor of Massachusetts.
They also have a former
Prime Minister of Canada.
So I really feel like Canopy
maybe buying that influence,
because that's this is
get down to business.
Weed's a commodity.
Everybody's gonna be able to grow it.
- By the way, it's not
the weed of yesteryear.
- So I've heard.
- I'm told.
All right up next, let's talk
more about recyclable shoes.
- [Bill] She told me by the way.
- [Kate] He told me, I
think he heard it from you.
- [Brian] You might have.
Adidas just released a new
running shoe, get this,
made from 100% recyclable material.
Once your shoes have fallen apart,
I assume they will fall apart,
you can return them to
Adidas where they recycle
for the components to
make a new pair of kicks.
Zion Williamson--
- [Bill] I was just gonna say.
- Should be there spokesperson.
I think he's probably
already signed with Nike.
What do you think, gimmick
Kate Rodgers, or real deal?
- It sounds like Adidas
wants to get this right.
I think it says they're
giving it to about 200 runners
to test them out, they're not
releasing the mass market yet
because they want to make
sure that they really---
- [Brian] How long do they last?
- That they really get this right.
Well whenever you're done,
you can hand them back
over to Adidas and I think
more broadly consumers
do care more and more about this.
We see more companies paying attention to
being eco friendly,
marketing things in this way.
- [Brian] Do they care?
- I think they do care.
- You know what they care about more?
Not rolling their ankle
or having their knees hurt
while they jog.
- Yeah of course, but now recycling
is becoming a big business right now.
That's pointing to that and as
we all know actor Jason Momoa
just shaved his beard
for the obvious reason
that he's promoting aluminum
as a recycling thing.
- Stop the presses, we
gotta end this show.
Khal Drogo has shaved, here's the thing.
Frank, don't come at this
as a business journalist.
You're a six foot five inch dude.
I don't know if you run,
I'm not quite your height.
Listen, we run, it hurts.
- [Frank] Absolutely.
- The shoes got to work
first and foremost.
- Zion Williamson was
perfect, a perfect example
that if the shoe can't
hold up it's a problem,
but I'm gonna be the cynic this time.
This is really differentiation.
Adidas has been trying to
increase it's market share.
A couple years ago they signed
a Kanye to a sneaker deal.
He's not really running anywhere,
but those sneakers sold like hot cakes.
- But those sneakers are so cool, yeah,
he doesn't need to run anywhere.
- Hey, you ran that marathon?
What's your shoe?
It's a gimmick, it's
the new Adidas gimmick.
- So like you said, recycle it.
- Finally, we're moving on.
remember how much hype Samsung's
foldable phone generated?
It's got a $2000 price tag,
but here's the problem some reviewer guys
who got this phone early
reported that it broke.
In fact our own Todd Haselton
CNBC found the screen
was flickering after just two days.
There's the video from
our own Todd Haselton.
Samsung, a real problem
or they just haven't figured it out yet?
Bill?
- I think it's a bigger problem right now.
Novelty is a big sales
item for technology.
This was novel to have the folding phone
but I think they're getting
ahead of themselves now.
They're rushing products to
market before they're ready
and they cost too much now by the way.
$1980 for a foldable phone.
It's becoming too complicated
and too expensive.
- Well call me old-fashioned,
but I don't need my phone to fold in half.
I need it to have a nice
camera, good reception,
and kind of look cool but
I don't care that much.
I wouldn't buy this.
I'm not who they're marketing to.
- I'm gonna tell you though,
this is the battle of the sexes though.
I will say this women and
men phone differently,
we keep our phone, we tend to keep it here
or in our like jeans pocket.
- Back pocket.
- Yeah, having a phone
that can flex a little bit
when you're a guy helps
out Frank, does it not?
- But the phone doesn't flex it, it folds.
- Yeah, but you could put it here.
The point is you could put
it maybe in this pocket
a little bit easier.
- I don't know about that part,
but here's the thing I actually
talked to Todd about this
a little bit deeper.
He says that the resolution
on the screen isn't as good
and the colors aren't as good
so if your whole selling point
is that it's a bigger screen
and the screen's not as
good as your other phone,
you might be missing the mark.
- Todd's the smart guy, I
don't know if he did this,
but I do know Samsung claimed
that some of the reviewers
accidentally, there's a protective screen,
they took it off thinking
it was removable.
- He didn't do that.
He did not do that.
- Okay, but apparently some people did
but it's not a removable thing.
They peeled the screen off.
- He actually tweeted up close photos
that he did not do that and his
screen still was flickering.
- Bottom line Kate Rogers,
yes or no, $2000 dollar phone?
- No, not for me.
But you you need to get it right.
We talked about apples
wireless charging mat
that they pulled from the market
because they said it wasn't ready.
This is a great example of
why it needs to be ready.
- I have a question.
Where's the button?
Kelly's got these, I press
a button and you and you
fall into the alligator pits.
Where are those buttons?
- And then I survive?
- You survived.
- All I can say is I'm exhausted now.
- Come on WEX one morning.
Trending stories of Bill Griffith.
- You bet I will.
- Okay, we'll see you
there in the morning Bill.
Thank you all. (laughing)
Coming up Foxconn fails to
deliver on jobs in Wisconsin.
What the governor plans
to do about that, next.
(upbeat music)
- What's going on?
I've done all sorts of
research, read earnings reports,
looked at chart patterns.
I even built my own
historic trading model.
- And you still not sure if
you want to make the trade?
- Exactly.
- Sounds like a case
of analysis paralysis.
- Is there a cure?
- TD Ameritrade trade desk.
They can help gut check your strategies
and answer all your toughest questions.
- Sounds perfect.
- See, your stress level was here
and I got you down to
here, I've done my job.
- [Announcer] Call for
a strategy gut check
with TD Ameritrade.
- [Announcer] Welcome to New York.
- [Announcer] Welcome to Las Vegas.
- [Announcer] Welcome to Paris.
- [Announcer] Welcome to your paradise.
- [Announcer] Business or pleasure,
ONEflight International
is connecting the world
with Book a Jet.
The BAJ.
When time matters, just BAJ it.
Simply enter your itinerary,
select from over 4000 private planes.
Browse interior photos, select, and pay.
Whether you're traveling alone
or with business associates
or a romantic getaway.
BAJ it on a luxurious private jet.
- What's your time worth?
- [Announcer] BAJ it.
- [Announcer] You dream,
you plan, you work.
Every hour, every day, every night.
There is no such thing
as a small business.
All business is personal.
How do you make a connection?
How do you grow your business?
We make it easy with high
quality affordable products
and innovative design
tools that make it simple
to promote and grow your business.
- [Announcer] Go to gotprint.com
to get 500 business cards
for $8.50 plus use promo code GP500BC
to get 10% off your first order.
- [Announcer] When buying a car,
we know there are a lot of questions.
- What's the mileage?
- How many previous owners?
- Has it been in any accidents?
- Is there room for twins?
- Or triplets?
- [Announcer] We all know
the most important question is always...
- Am I getting a good deal?
- [Announcer] CarGurus has the answer.
CarGurus gives every car a deal rating
from great to overpriced and
sorts the best ones first
making it fast and easy
to find great deals
from top-rated dealers near you.
Find your great deal today at CarGurus.
(upbeat music)
- All right, welcome back to The Exchange.
Foxconn back in focus today
with it's Wisconsin jobs pledge
now being called into question.
Governor Tony Evers telling reporters
that he wants to renegotiate the deal
saying the company will not
be creating the 13000 jobs
that it pledged.
For more on this big story
let's bring in one of
the reporters that has followed that story
from the beginning.
Rick Rimmel business reporter
for the Milwaukee Journal Sentinel.
All right Rick thank you
very much for joining us.
I mean CNBC was there, we
were in Kenosha as well.
A lot of promise,
what appears to be falling
through the cracks here?
- Well you know we're all
sort of waiting to see
whether the Foxconn will come through on
what it has said it would do
and I think it's fair
to say that the progress
toward those goals has been slow.
- How slow as in slow we're
getting there eventually
or slow as in the car
is not actually moving
down the highway?
- The car is moving, it might
be moving at I don't know,
25 miles an hour or something.
They've made multiple changes
to their plans for plant.
Initially they said it was
going to be what they call a
generation 10.5 flat screen plant,
which is the largest most
expensive type of plant
in this industry.
Finally, middle of last
year they acknowledged no,
we're not going to build
a generation 10 plant.
It's going to be a generation six plant,
smaller less costly and
then a month or two ago
it looked like they were
thinking about backing away
from building a factory
at all in Wisconsin.
Then the President, Donald Trump,
gets on the phone to Terry
Gou, Chairman of Foxconn.
All of a sudden within
hours Foxconn comes out
with a statement saying yes we will build
this smaller type of factory.
Foxconn continues to maintain
it'll create 13000 jobs.
A lot of people in Wisconsin just don't,
they're not buying it.
- I was gonna say listen Rick,
do you believe and the
sources you talk to?
Heck, do your neighbors
believe that this plant
will ever get built?
- Personally yeah, I think
there's a good chance
that something is going to be built there.
I mean they already are, they
have construction underway
so they've prepared a very
large like, I don't know.
It might be 60 acre site that
has gravel compressed down
tight to be the bed for the
foundation of the plant.
They let contracts about
two three weeks ago
for like 34 million dollars
worth of preparatory work
for the actual building construction
and that part is under
way as far as I can tell
and they say that this summer
they will start building
actual physical vertical
construction itself.
- When they do that you, let us know,
you take pictures, we'll
get you back on CNBC.
Rick Romell, thank you very much.
- You bet, thank you Brian.
- All right.
Coming up, the Sears drama.
You thought it was over, it's not.
The company is suing former
CEO Eddie Lampert and others,
get this, including Treasury
Secretary Stephen Mnuchin.
Sears versus Stephen, next.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Feel that?
That's the beat of global markets.
The rhythm of the world.
But to us, it's the pace of tomorrow.
With ingenuity, technologies,
and markets expertise
we create the possible
and when you do that
you don't chase the face of tomorrow.
You set it.
NASDAQ, rewrite tomorrow.
- [Announcer] At Angie's
List you can find any type
of home pro and check their reputation
by reading verified reviews
from your neighbors.
Instantly request quotes
from multiple pros
at the same time.
And browse special deals on
all kinds of home projects.
At Angie's List it's
free to find all the pros
you need to know from
landscapers to roofers
and everything in between.
Go to AngiesList.com today.
- [Announcer] For great offers
visit your local Jaguar retailer today.
- And time for the Closing Countdown,
let's have a look at the markets.
- [Announcer] Strategy in
the final minutes of trading.
- [Woman] Let's take a
look at how we finished up
the day on Wall Street.
- [Announcer] Catch the Closing Countdown,
today and every weekday on Closing Bell.
Sponsored by E-Trade, the
original place to invest online.
- If something happened to
you, what would happen to them?
Their home, their education, their future.
You need life insurance and chances are
SelectQuote can help you get it
for less than a dollar a day.
- [Announcer] SelectQuote found Jacob, 40,
a $500000 policy for only $19 a month
and SelectQuote found his
wife Wendy a $500000 policy
for only $17 a month.
- Our secret?
At select quote we
aggressively comparison shop
up to 10 highly rated
companies to find you
the company with the best rates.
- [Announcer] We found Gary, 35,
a one million dollar policy
for only $22 a month.
- Why pay more?
Give your family the security they need
at a price you can afford.
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-289-6042
or go to SelectQuote.com now
and get the insurance your family needs.
- [Man] At a price you can afford.
SelectQuote, we shop, you save.
(upbeat music)
- Well just when you
thought that it was over,
the Sears drama is resurfacing.
The company is now suing
former CEO Eddie Lampert
for allegedly stealing billions of dollars
from the corporation.
The lawsuit alleges that Lampert
along with Sears biggest shareholders
unduly benefited from deals
that occurred under his watch.
The suit names other defendants as well.
Besides Lampert they include get this,
Treasury Secretary Stephen Mnuchin
and Hedge Fund Manager Bruce Berkowitz.
Sears Holdings filed for
bankruptcy this past October.
All right coming up,
only one-third of American
states require students
to graduate with a personal finance class.
Just one class.
Your next guest says that's a big problem.
She'll join us on what her
group is doing about it, next.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Every day visionaries
are creating the future.
So every day we put our latest technology
and unrivaled network to work.
The United States Postal Service
makes more E-commerce deliveries to homes
than anyone else in the country.
- [Announcer] Are you over the age of 50
and considering buying an
annuity in the next 60 days?
I have some important news for you.
Don't buy an annuity until you understand
the pros and cons of annuities.
Call now for this free book
on maximizing your income
in retirement, Annuity Do's
and Don'ts For Baby Boomers.
From leading financial firm JD Milberg.
That's right, free.
This book reveals little-known
truths about annuities
and simple to understand terms.
Grab a pen right now because
we're about to offer you
this free book that unlocks
the five little-known truths
we believe baby boomers
and seniors should know
before buying an annuity.
And it's free.
Call 800-926-1155 now.
As a bonus, we'll also throw
in a free Annuity Rate Report.
We research too numerous products
and summarized rates and
benefits of annuities.
All from Sentinel Security
Life Insurance company.
Call 800-926-1155, that's 800-926-1155.
Call now.
♪ I want it all ♪
♪ And I want it now ♪
- [Announcer] With the
Grubhub delivery app.
(whistling)
If you want all, you can get it all.
Grubhub, restaurants you love, delivered.
(phone ringing)
- We still have service?
Call the insurance company.
- It's them calling us.
- It's gonna be a week
before they can get
through on these roads.
- Shh!
Sorry, I didn't catch that.
- I said ask how soon they can be here.
- Not you.
- Right now?
- What's now?
- He says they're
surveying our property now.
- They're probably at the wrong house.
- I don't see any hovering.
- His name's hovering?
- Look up.
- [Announcer] By using machine learning
and analytics to automate claims
Cognizant is helping
insurance companies advance
how they serve even the
hardest to reach customers.
- Cool.
- [Announcer] Every year our analysts
visit thousands of companies
in a multitude of countries
where we get to know the people that drive
a company's growth and
gain new perspectives.
That's why we go beyond the numbers.
T. Rowe Price, invest with confidence.
- Next time you think about buying a stock
you need to ask yourself a question.
Add this to your homework checklist.
Could Amazon come in and
destroy the company's margins?
If so lower your expectations.
(upbeat music)
- All right, welcome back.
A new op-ed ad on CNBC
highlights America's growing need
for financial education programs,
especially for economically
disadvantaged children.
It is part of our financial
education initiative called
Invest in You: Ready, Set, Grow.
And it's in partnership with
micro investing app Acorns
and joining us now is
the author of that piece,
Nan Morrison the President
and CEO the Council
For Economic Education.
Also a member of our CNBC
Financial Wellness Council.
It's amazing Nan, you
can be in high school
and take classes on the Peloponnesian War
and not understand how
to balance a checkbook.
Why?
(laughs)
- That is quite amazing.
- No offense to the Peloponnesian War.
- Exactly, exactly.
But we don't do a good job of
getting financial education
into our nation's K through 12 schools
and that's the mission of
our organization to do that,
to teach those K through 12
kids about personal finance
and economics so they can
make better decisions,
so they know how to manage their money,
to balance the checkbook,
to make decisions about
a credit card or a loan,
to make good decisions about those.
- Now without getting into the
politics of school districts
and unions but it's hard to get classes,
new classes created.
What's the best way to do that
and what's been the holdup
for just saying hey,
maybe you don't need
that 14th history class.
Let's talk about how not to go bankrupt.
- One of the great things
about what we do is
we teachers and we help
them with the content,
we give them lessons
and we also teach them
how to integrate it into the everyday life
of their classroom.
So think of creating a mini
economy for little kids
in a K through five classroom.
Think about integrating it into math
instead of those crazy problems
about the Amtrak trains.
How many times have you thought about
how fast that other
train is coming at you?
No, but you think about what
your investments are doing.
So we should be teaching
those examples in math
or another business oriented classes.
- And the weird thing about
this area in particular is
you've got Wall Street,
literally Wall Street,
I mean the physical street
with the New York Stock Exchange on.
- It's right there.
- Blocks away.
Our kids with nothing and no education.
How do we bring those...
They're physically this close,
how do we make them work for each other?
Right?
It benefits everybody
when everybody benefits.
- It does.
Well, there are a couple
of things that we're doing.
We're running Family Financial
Literacy nights at schools
where volunteers can come with
parents and teachers and kids
to learn about money and
we also have a new program,
Invest In Girls, which
not only helps girls
to get introduced to the
language and grammar of finance
but also takes them to places.
So it introduces them
to the world of finance,
to people like you and me
and some of the women here
at CNBC, the great ones.
So that they can see there's a possibility
of a really interesting
career working in finance.
- And you point out that
families of professionals,
their kids have 30 million more words
than kids on welfare.
A lot of those words
are financial related.
Financial words can be scary
sometimes even to adults.
Right?
How do we de-intimidize, is that a word?
(laughing)
- How about demystify?
- Thank you very much.
- Any time.
How do we demystify or
make finance less scary,
how about that?
- Yeah, I think we just
need to talk about it more.
It's just like any language.
Once you start speaking
it, learning the words,
it's less scary and you don't need to know
all the complicated stuff.
You just need to know like
hello, please, thank you,
and where's the bathroom,
and if we can teach the
kids the basic language
and grammar of finance
when they're little,
same as when we teach them
everything else, then it's easy.
Then they're not afraid
to ask the question.
- [Brian] Or make up words
during segments on vocabulary.
- [Nan] They can do that too.
- Nan Morrison, great stuff.
Important topic, thank you
very much for joining us.
- Thanks so much for having me here.
- Of course, I don't want
to de-intimidize you.
(laughing)
For more you could visit cnbc.com/