- You are totally off base here.
- [Announcer] Log on and
join our live conversation.
- I can't believe I'm saying
this, I do agree with you.
- [Announcer] DBL starts right now.
- [Producer] Three, two.
- Welcome to Daily Blast Live.
It is Tuesday, May 7th, we are live
and we're talking about what
you're talking about right now.
I'm here with Tory, Jeff, Al and I am Sam.
Let's get started.
We have our brand new interview
with pop sensation's Pentatonix,
joining us from their
first ever world tour.
Plus we have wedding
guest fashion secrets.
We're telling you how
you can look your best,
without, of course, upstaging
the bride, c'mon on now.
All that in minutes, the
stars brought their craziest,
most over-the-top looks ever
to this year's Met Gala.
The theme was camp, notes of fashion,
and everyone was expected
to pull out all the stops,
but hold up, what is camp?
Well, it is defined as the
love of the un-natural,
of artifice and exaggeration,
basically everything
that is fabulous, ironic, or extra.
So let's get to the fashion,
and the title this year
for the most lit, definitely
goes to Katy Perry,
whether ya hate it, or ya like it,
she definitely is having people talking.
She wore this illuminated chandelier look,
it was created for her by
Jeremy Scott of Moschino.
Kim Kardashian showed off her figure,
in this skin tight latex corseted dress,
- [Jeff] Looks like a bottle of perfume.
- [Sam] by Thierry Mugler,
who came out of retirement
to create the look, which took, you guys,
eight months to complete, by the way.
It appeared to be dripping
wet, thanks in part
to the crystals and shimmery material.
Katie Holmes and Jamie Foxx
made their public debut
as a couple last night.
While they didn't hit
the pink carpet together,
the couple did pose for photos
with one another inside,
and Kendall and Kylie Jenner
broke out the feathers
for their camp looks.
Kendall wore bright orange
feathered Versace gown,
while Kylie opted for a
lilac look, with a fur stohl
I'm hoping faux, and a matching wig.
Actress Janelle Monae
embraced wearable art,
with this custom Christian Siriano look,
and the eye even winked as she
walked down the pink carpet.
Come on now.
Lady Gaga served up multiple
looks for her grand entrance
to the event, all created
by Brandon Maxwell.
It started off with a huge pink dress,
that took an army of men
with umbrellas to wrangle,
she then stripped down to a black dress,
followed by a skin tight pink dress,
and then it all ended up with her posing
in her underwear, here it comes.
Yes girl, with huge platform shoes.
Serena Williams wore
this stunning neon yellow
Versace gown, with pink
feathery leaf accents,
and she paired her look with neon Nikes.
Jennifer Lopez sparkled in
this beaded Versace dress,
with a plunging neckline
and fringe detailing.
She wore a matching headpiece,
and of course A-rod,
I mean, Tory, makes a good
accessory, am I right?
- [Tory] Mmm bah!
- [Sam] Okay
Lupita Nyong'o embraced the
rainbow, with this Versace gown,
with pink star pattern
and rainbow ruffles,
and check out the gold
afro picks in her hair,
with raised fist logos, yes.
Jared Leto, my favorite,
had the best accessory of the night.
A custom replica of his head.
He brought it along while
rocking this red Gucci dress.
Kacey Musgraves looked like a barbie doll,
in this hot pink Moschino leather dress,
pairing it with a blow dryer
bag and cat eye shades.
Cardi B won the award
for the biggest train,
with this red feathered, Tom Brown gown.
The 10 foot long train, nearly
took over the pink carpet,
and Cierra might have won
best hair of the night,
I think she won, let's be honest,
with this very extra, gorgeous afro.
She also wore a custom Peter
Dundas emerald green crown,
because she is a queen,
and Zendaya had a fairy
tale moment at the gala,
transforming into Cinderella,
in this Tommy Hilfiger
ball gown, with white poofy sleeves,
and a skirt that lit up,
yes, yes, yes.
- Sam, you drink some water, we'll talk.
(laughter)
- Are you, I actually
looked at Al, or Al, I
looked at Jeff midway,
and your eyes were closed.
- Dude, I was out.
(laughter)
I was thinking about cheese and crackers,
and what I'm gonna do tonight.
- You know what I was thinking?
I'm like this coffee's
bitter, I should think about
a different kind of coffee. (laughs)
- I guess I'm the only one,
- I was kinda into it Sam.
- really appreciated the
looks as art.
Say what you want.
- It took, all those people
got together to entertain us,
- I agree.
- like that's all,
I mean it's just like
somebody's gotta shake it up
a little bit, we all can't
wear khakis and polo shirts,
somebody's gotta shake it
up and push the envelope
a little bit, that's what art does.
- I'm for universal uniforms everyday.
- Like Star Trek?
- Yes!
- Boring!
- Boring, I wear
the same thing to work
everyday, that's fine with me.
- Yeah, that's a man of a certain age,
I'd do the same thing, I
got those green sweat pants,
they could walk to work themselves.
(laughter)
- I've noticed that too.
- Now, Tory, do you have a favorite,
even though I guess you were bored by it?
- No, no, I did have a favorite,
Ezra Miller, I though
absolutely nailed camp.
And this is a guy that is gender fluid,
and he used prosthetics as the eyes,
- Wow!
- And you really get that kid,
- Wait, wait, wait,
those weren't real eyes?
- I know, I don't know
what I said it like that.
(laughter)
Those were real eyes.
But it's about the artifice
and the exaggeration,
and I like the gender
fluidity, that was all over
the red carpet,
- [Sam] It was.
- the pink carpet, excuse me.
- Yeah, I loved that too,
I'm with you, Al?
- I'mma nod my head and pretend like
I know what artifice means.
- [Sam] (laughs)
- The artificialness,
like it's fake, like camp is very kitschy
and fake and over done.
- [Sam] Right, now.
- Now, what does kitschy mean?
- [Sam] Same thing.
- Campy, yeah.
- [Al] Okay, thank you.
- Now Al, we do call
you Al Fashion Jackson,
- Yes ma'am.
- so you had
to have a favorite.
- Oh, my boy Nick Jonas.
I mean that is like
- [Sam] Your boy, huh?
- Yeah, we go way back, but
I just like, he looks like,
- He looks like little finger.
- He looks like a waiter at
The Cheesecake Factory, doesn't he?
- [Tory] Yeah. (laughs)
- [Jeff] Like Dubai.
- [Al] Yeah, like,
- [Sam] In Dubai.
- [Al] makes me hungry.
- [Tory] A lot of people, yes.
- The Dubai Cheesecake Factory.
- That's it, that's it,
- That's a good one.
- that's their uniforms.
- You nailed it,
you nailed it, Jeff,
do you have a favorite?
- Well, listen, I know everyone
hates Kylie and Kendall,
the Kardashians, or Jenners I should say,
check them out, they look
terrific, but I don't like
that they didn't walk with their dates
down the red or the pink carpet.
(laughter)
- That's a good one, that's a good one.
Hey, I'm gonna, listen,
I think all the work
that these fashion designers
put into these outfits,
I really wanna give
them some credit, I know
- [Al] Sam, who was your favorite?
- [Sam] Janelle Monae,
that is a work of art.
That dress is art, you
guys, and then again,
with the gender fluidity,
I think that Jared Leto
with that gorgeous red Gucci gown,
and then who doesn't love
a severed head as a purse.
- I really didn't even
notice he was wearing a gown,
and I think that's the way,
if you don't want people
to notice, just carry another head.
I really did not notice
he was wearing a gown,
till you said something.
- [Jeff] Wait, that's a purse?
- I believe it was a purse.
- I think it was,
or an accessory, but he
held it like a purse.
- [Sam] He held it like a purse.
- [Tory] He sure did.
- [Sam] I, hey, I'm all for it.
- [Al] So we don't know.
- [Tory] Lookin' good Jared.
(laughter)
I don't know.
- [Al] Now what if Mark
showed up with that purse of your head?
- [Jeff] Fashion.
(laughter)
- [Sam] Yeah, exactly, fashion.
All right, let's get this
next story, an update
to the college admission scandal.
Lori Loughlin's defense might
have just gotten a boost,
thanks to the University of
Southern California's crew team.
Teams that reports this ad for the team
is posted all over campus.
You can see it says no
experience, no problem.
Some say the poster could
help Lori's defense,
that her daughters lack of
experience doesn't matter,
the team doesn't require
experience to join.
Lori of course, is
accused of paying bribes
to pass her daughters
off as athletic recruits,
in order to get them into USC.
Now Tory, I know you are our legal eagle,
this makes my blood boil.
- [Tory] Yeah.
- Because if Lori Loughlin
is going to use this
as her defense, she's
suggesting that all of us
are stupid.
- [Tory] Yep.
- She's suggesting that
everybody out there
that has worked hard to
get into a university,
whether you are an athlete,
whether you are as a scholar,
again is stupid, so
could this work for her?
- Yeah, it could go both ways, right?
It could backfire completely,
because it's so obvious.
We have her on tape, being
like, "Take a picture
"of them on rowing
machines, and send it in."
We know the real thing.
She insulted so many people
when she plead not guilty.
That's really where she made her mistake
as we talked before.
Now it only takes one person, to be like,
"Maybe she didn't know though."
So they are using the loophole defense,
it's a long shot, it's a Hail Mary,
but it's worked before,
and all she wants to do
is avoid prison time.
- [Jeff] And I think she is gonna do that.
- [Tory] You do?
- And I don't think so.
- I think she's gonna, listen.
She's not calling us
stupid, our judicial system
is calling us stupid, the
lawyers that defend her
are calling us stupid,
because if she gets off,
it's just proof that our
system does not work.
- [Sam] You're right.
- And that's what's gonna
happ, she's gonna walk,
- But our.
- because you could buy
your way out of jail if
you have enough money.
- And many would argue our system works,
in the opposite way, because
you do have women of color
that are locked up for, oh
I'm sorry, sending their
kid to a public school
in a different zip code.
So Al, does the judicial system
work, or does it not work,
depending on how you look
at it, inside what lens?
- I think it's working perfectly.
- [Sam] Unfortunately.
- It caters to the rich,
I mean, if you are rich,
you don't see jail as a deterrent.
Like, anybody that's got some money,
you can get a good attorney,
Tory you know this,
the reason lawyers cost
different amounts of money
and some are free, is a free
lawyer is gonna be like,
"Sam, take the deal.",
where as a great lawyer
is gonna go through everything.
"Did they say the, or thee
when they Mirandized you?"
They're gonna figure out
- Wow.
- and all they need is one thing,
and that's why you pay that money,
and if you have money,
you're gonna get that lawyer,
and they're gonna get you off,
so that's why Jeff feels like that,
'cause it's true.
- Yeah, it's disappointing, shame on her,
and shame on the judicial system,
- Yeah.
- We need reform,
and we need reform now.
DBL's live, we will
bring you breaking news
as soon as it happens.
Coming up, Acapella never sounded so good.
The band Pentatonix takes
time to chat with DBL
in the middle of their
first ever world tour.
Then an eye opening study
all about sunscreen.
A surprising new findings,
that might make you
rethink the kind of sunblock you use,
and you, the viewer, are our fifth host,
and we want your take on
this controversial story.
A bartender is in trouble,
after prosecutors say
she over served a man,
right before he went
on a shooting rampage.
Should she be charged with a crime?
Send in your comments
right now, we are live,
and we're gonna read them next.
(exciting music)
(snappy pop music)
♪ I'm feelin' good. ♪
- How ever you take your business card,
make the most of it with more
shapes, stocks, and finishes
from Vista Print.
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, I'm feelin' good. ♪
- Now is the time to
try 500 standard cards
starting at just $9.99
with promo code BCNOW.
♪ I'm feelin' good. ♪
Own the now, with Vista Print.
- [Announcer] Next Tuesday.
- This one time.
- [Announcer] On ET.
- Luckily they don't finish the sentence.
- [Announcer] It's Entertainment Tonight,
American Pie reunion, next Tuesday on ET.
- Tonight at 7:30 on WUSA 9.
- Why not take the whole family
(intense music)
out for a geological thrill.
Only at Luray Caverns.
What will you discover?
- You've been chosen,
and everyone is watching.
You've been anticipating this moment,
since the last time you
came to Uncle Julio's.
Experience the unforgettable moment
of smashing a chocolate pinata.
Make fresh memories,
only at Uncle Julio's.
- WUSA 9 wants you to win
tickets to see Kidz Bop
live in concert on July 14th.
(energetic music)
Text Kidz bop to 65047.
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm Dan from MarketPro Homebuyers,
and we wanna buy your home.
- My husband and I were
faced with the decision
of what to do with my father's home.
The house required a lot of work.
That's when I found MarketPro Homebuyers.
Dan visited our home, and within minutes,
he gave us a quote.
It was so easy.
Dan even helped pay to pack and move us.
MarketPro Homebuyers
truly helped my family,
when we did not know what to do.
- [Dan] Call us today at 301-799-7355.
- Around here, even a little rain makes us
down right giddy.
That's because we've seen it do some
pretty spectacular things.
See for yourself at Luray Caverns.
What will you discover?
- [Announcer] A catfish exposed.
- You've stolen his identity.
- [Announcer] Will all their questions,
- Why our family?
- [Announcer] Finally be answered?
- How'd you get the pictures
from the inside of their house?
- [Announcer] Next Dr. Phil.
- Today at four, followed
by WUSA 9 news at five.
(exciting music)
- Welcome back to DBL, it
is time for fifth host,
when we talk about what
you're talkin' about.
A Texas bartender has
been arrested, and charged
for over serving a man, the night he shot
and killed eight people.
Lindsay Glass is accused
of violating a state law
by selling alcohol to an
intoxicated or insane person.
Police say she should have
known to stop serving the man,
because he appeared drunk, and armed.
Turned out his blood alcohol level
was more than four times the legal limit.
After leaving the bar, the man killed
his estranged wife, and seven others,
before dying in a police shootout.
The bartender now faces
up to a year in prison,
a fine of $500 or both.
Should she be charged with a crime?
Now, she wouldn't be charged for murder,
this would be a misdemeanor, so to speak,
I just wanna clarify that.
- Sad story, Bobby from Facebook says,
"I think the bartender is
responsible for keeping
"patrons from becoming
unreasonably intoxicated,
"but only the shooter is
responsible for murder."
Bobby, great take, you used
the perfect word there,
unreasonably intoxicated,
and with your BAC at four
times the legal limit,
that means that you
probably can't stand up.
The fact that this man was
armed, at least to the point
where she was aware of it,
I think that she should
be implicated in some way.
I don't know, my whole thing,
I'm not about throwing people in jail.
I mean, this could be used
to teach other people.
I mean, you shouldn't have
to teach people not to serve
drunk people with guns, but some people
gotta learn that lesson, I guess.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, Patty from Facebook
says, "Bars are just out to make money.
"They don't care about
the dangers of alcohol.
"This needs to change."
I know, Sam, you were a bartender,
and you can speak.
- [Sam] Jeff too.
- And Jeff too, and there
are very strict laws
about serving people that
you can reasonably see
are over served.
- Oh they make an example of that.
- Yeah.
- [Jeff] Oh yeah.
- In Los Angeles, it's
a corporation called
the ABC, they train you, they make sure
to let you know about those red flags,
and God forbid you over serve someone,
both Jeff and I have cut many people off,
but we both seen people,
- [Jeff] Oh yeah.
- our colleagues,
dragged out of that bar in handcuffs,
to make a point,
- [Tory] For serving.
- because of a DUI,
you could kill someone,
you could kill yourself.
- Right, they don't bring
them out the back door,
they make sure all the servers see it,
they bring him out the front door,
they make an example,
like they handcuff 'em,
so it is a big deal.
- You're serving a drug,
- And I think it should
and I, Yeah
- Tory, alcohol's a drug.
- And I think you should be liable,
if you're a gun maker and you sell
to an underage person by
mistake, you're liable,
and they shoot people, you're also liable,
so I think she broke the law.
- And I do wanna set this up though.
We've talked about this story,
we set it up for a minute.
We don't know if this guy
was coming up to the bar,
we don't know the whole,
what was going on,
obviously I've seen someone
fall out of a chair,
I know to cut them off.
If they're all over the place,
and they're coming to get drinks,
I don't know.
I'm not responsible.
- [Sam] Yeah, are they
drinking in the bathroom,
- Right, we don't,
- are they properly trained,
- Did they drink before they came,
so there's a lot that goes in this,
we can't just speculate
on what the bartender
did or did not see.
But Marcus from Facebook says,
"How would the bartender
have known what this guy
"was going to do after he left the bar?
"Hold people accountable
for their own actions."
Marcus, I love you for saying that.
Accountability, I think a word
that has been erased from the dictionary.
Be accountable for your own actions,
not because you're fifth
grade teacher gave you an F
and called you a name, that's why you went
and shot up everybody,
not because the bartender
over served you, that's why
you went and shot up everybody?
Hold this man accountable.
Does this lady need to do her job
depending on the circumstances?
Maybe.
This man's accountable.
Not anybody else.
He's the one who killed eight people,
let's not forget that.
- Got it, all right.
- Sorry.
- Oh, great takes everybody,
thanks for writing in.
Coming up on DBL, eat
better, sleep better.
Uh-oh, I'm already sold.
We've got the top foods
that a nutritionist says
will help you get a good nights rest,
and pop sensation Pentatonix,
joins us for the first time,
find out why their unique acapella style
is wowing audiences
everywhere, when we come back.
♪ You just want attention ♪
♪ I knew from the start ♪
- In the connected world we live in,
our personal information is everywhere.
What happens if that information
gets in the hands of criminals?
- Someone benefited from this.
We were the ones on the hook for it.
We can't pay a $50,000 bill.
- Cyber criminals around
the world keep finding
new ways to steal your
personal information,
And it could be right from
your personal computer
or smart phone.
That's why LifeLock includes
the power of Norton.
For even more protection,
for your identity
and your devices, where so much
of your personal information lives.
- Knowing that Norton and
LifeLock are on my side,
makes me feel even more
confident about the protection
that I have for my identity.
- Monitoring your credit isn't enough
to see if your identity
is being used by thieves.
LifeLock helps you see more threats
like your information on the dark web.
And now, with the power of Norton,
we help defend your personal information
on your devices, from
ransomware, spyware, and more.
And if you have an identity theft problem,
a US-based restoration
agent will work to fix it.
- There's a whole team of people
that are working on my behalf.
- Only LifeLock members
are covered by LifeLocks
powerful Million Dollar
Protection Package.
Including reimbursement of stolen funds
and personal expenses up
to the limits of your plan,
and lawyers and experts
if that's what it takes.
- I was covered through my membership,
and I received a check
for approximately $1,200.
- Join for as low as $9.99 per month,
and get 30 days free
with promo code, JoinNow.
All memberships include identity
threat detection and alerts
with agents working to fix issues,
LifeLocks Million Dollar
Protection Package,
and award winning, Norton
Security Protection
for up to five devices.
- I've got two industry leaders
to help protect my
identity and my devices.
LifeLock with Norton.
- Call 1-800-293-6019 or
visit LifeLockDeal.com
Use promo code, JoinNow
to get your 30 days free,
and free shredder with annual membership.
Call right now.
(exciting music)
♪ Goodbye everybody ♪
♪ I've got to go ♪
♪ Got to leave you all
behind and face the truth ♪
- What you just heard
involved no instruments,
only five voices, that's
acapella band Pentatonix,
and they just kicked off
their first world tour.
I caught up with three
of the bands five members
in today's chatting with the stars.
(random tones and static)
Scott, Mitch, and Kevin,
welcome to Daily Blast Live.
Pentatonix are about to
kick off a world tour,
but I'd like to talk to
you about your early days.
You guys made your mark covering
popular songs on YouTube.
Is there a song or artist
you have not covered yet,
but you've got your sights set on?
- We haven't really done
a Taylor Swift song.
We tried.
- Yeah, we could
do the new one.
- Yeah.
- Exactly, yeah, that'd
be really, really fun.
- You guys have kicked
off your world tour,
yet there are still some
critics who still say
you guys are just a cover band.
So how do you respond to
that kind of criticism?
- I don't think it really bothers us,
at the end of the day, like
we take songs that we love
and do them in a way
that only we can do them,
which is a very special ability that we've
kind of created over the past years,
and it's been really, really fun
getting into original music,
it's a journey, and we're just so thankful
that we get to (mumbles)
- I want to play a
rapid fire question game
with you all, I've decided I'm callin' it,
the Aca-Answers with
Pentatonix, so are you ready?
(laughter)
- Very ready.
- Let's go.
- Let's do it.
(laughter)
- First one, who in the band
is always late to rehearsal?
- Oh, Kirsti.
- I'm always like five minutes late too.
- Yeah, but yeah.
- Who is the mom of the group?
- Kevin, I think.
- Oh, that's nice.
- Yeah, you're the most
organized and things.
- Okay, well, thank you.
I appreciate that.
- Who calls their mom the most?
- You do!
- I call my mom everyday.
- That's cute, good son
award, good son award.
Who's always taking selfies of themself?
(camera shutter)
- Probably us.
- Or Kirstie.
(camera shutter)
- Oh Kirstie does take a lot too.
- Yeah Kirstie takes a lot.
- Yeah she takes a lot of selfies
- Who's always snacking?
- Snacking?
- I feel like you or me.
- Ah, me.
- Scott, probably Scott.
(laughter)
- And the last one,
now this is as a group,
what's your favorite song to perform?
- I think Bohemian Rhapsody.
♪ Is this the real life ♪
- [Scott] Yeah, it's a crowd pleaser.
- All right, so okay,
since that's your favorite,
do you mind giving me a little snippet?
- Oh my God,
- Oh my God.
- it's hard enough with five people,
we're missing some.
- We only have three
with us right now.
- It would sound like nothing
if the three of us did it.
- I would offer my
services, but believe me,
your ears would be damaged for life.
(laughter)
It'd be awful.
Thank you guys so much,
Scott, Kevin, and Mitch,
three of the five members of Pentatonix,
who are on a world tour right now.
Check these guys out if
they're in a city near you,
you will not regret it.
Thanks guys, you've been awesome.
- Thank you, you too.
- Thank you, appreciate it.
- We'll be right back.
- Promotional consideration
is brought to you by,
(static)
(click)
This is the kind of card
that has America talking.
With it, people with Medicare
are getting all-in-one
coverage for their doctor
visits, hospital care,
prescription drugs, and more.
This kind of insurance
called Medicare Part C,
may also cover dental care,
eyeglasses, hearing aids,
fitness programs, vitamins,
even healthy meals
and rides to the doctors.
With this kind of
coverage, you do not need
a Medicare Supplement insurance plan.
You will access your benefits
through your Medicare
part C plan, for one low,
and often times zero dollar
monthly plan premium.
You deserve to get the most
from your Medicare benefits.
Call now for free
information that may help you
get more coverage for less money.
There is no obligation to enroll.
Whether for yourself, or someone you love,
call the number on the
screen now, call now.
- DC isn't for the faint of heart,
we're strivers, we're thrivers,
and even without
representation, we have a voice,
and we will be heard.
We're more than just idealists,
we're original, we know what's right,
and we know what's real.
- And you deserve news
that's as real as you are.
- We are WUSA 9, and every night,
we tell your stories,
because real matters.
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm Dan from MarketPro Homebuyers,
and we wanna buy your home.
Don't make repairs, don't pay commissions,
for a no obligation
offer, call 301-799-7355,
or visit marketprohomebuyers.com.
- After I got hit by a semi,
I didn't know trucking companies
were gonna try to take advantage of me.
- I didn't know signing papers
from the insurance company
could ruin my case.
- I didn't know having
a lawyer with experience
would make such a big
difference with my settlement.
- We do know, at Saiontx and
Kirk, we know injury law,
and we know how to get you,
the most money possible.
- Call Saiontx and Kirk,
you'll never pay any money up front.
When you need a lawyer, you have a lawyer.
- Call 1-800-lawyers or
visit youhavealawyer.com
If you have a phone, you have a lawyer.
- With Cox, you get
everything you wanna watch
in one place, using the voice remote.
- Show me action (ding, ding)
- Even a ninny like me can figure it out,
with streaming apps, you miss live events,
and waste time searching for shows.
- Not this one, that one?
- It's clear that Cox
is the better choice,
just like it's clear
that the teleprompter guy
things I'm a booboohead
who steal parking spots.
(upbeat pop music)
- Get live TV, great apps,
and on demand from Cox,
starting at $79.99 a month.
- You've tried so many moisturizers,
but one blows them all outta the water.
Hydro Boost with hyaluronic
acid to plump skin cells
so it bounces back.
Neutrogena and try our hydrating makeup.
- CBS tonight,
Camp Big Brother is filled with wildlife,
and the smells of nature.
- Ewwww!
But it's not all fun and games.
- This is serious business.
- Two house guests are
nominated for eviction.
- This is my worst nightmare.
- And it's a power of veto
food fight for their lives.
- Aaaah!
- New Big Brother, CBS tonight.
- This is nice.
- How far would you go for love?
- So, where you from?
- Nigeria.
- Wow, that's a heck of a commute, huh?
- Bob Hearts Abishola, CBS this fall.
(exciting music)
- Welcome back to DBL,
making the right food choices
can be tough, in today's so nutritious,
sponsored by SoClean,
Tory Shulman meets up
with a nutritionist to learn about foods
that'll help you sleep better.
Take a look.
- Hey guys, we are here
with Sara Peternell,
she is a holistic nutritionist,
at Family Nutrition Services,
and she is here to tell us,
how food can affect your sleep.
I know, mind blown.
Talk to me about how sleep
and eating go together,
'cause I never thought about that.
- Absolutely, who hasn't
had trouble sleeping,
- Yes!
- at one point or another,
I know I have.
- What are some specific foods,
so I know to stock?
- There are foods that are rich
in an amino acid called tryptophan.
The first one is--
- Turkey, yeah, yeah.
- you said it.
Exactly, that's why everybody's
so sleepy on Thanksgiving.
- Right.
- But nuts are a really good
accessible source of tryptophan.
Almonds, brazil nuts, walnuts,
just eating a quarter
cup of these per day,
can really help to boost
your tryptophan levels,
which converts in the body to serotonin.
- Wow, so you'd be nuts not to do it.
- You would be totally
nuts not to do (laughs).
- Sorry.
All right, so what else other than nuts?
- So my favorite one of
all is actually cherries.
Cherries, when they contain melatonin,
they actually just help to contribute
to your bodies own
production of melatonin.
This sleep hormone is one of the hormones
that regulates like our circadian rhythm.
- So cherries, nuts, what else?
- Fish, is actually a sleep remedy,
- Really?
- and it's not thought of,
but it should be because
it has a very high level
of vitamin B6.
- And B6 helps you sleep?
- Vitamin B6 is actually
important for that conversion
of tryptophan to serotonin.
- Oh, I see.
- So when we're talking about
nuts, you know, we use the
amino acid in our bodies
to convert to serotonin,
but if you're low in B6,
that conversion doesn't take
place quite as naturally.
- I want to thank Sarah Peternell
for dealing with me first
off, and for teaching us
some accessible things
you can do right now,
at the grocery store,
to help your own body
naturally get to some Z's.
- I guess I need to stock up on cherries,
'cause momma hasn't been sleepin'.
- You've been having some trouble,
and she also mentioned to me yogurt.
So if you make a smoothie
and include all of this,
yogurt, cherries, walnuts,
you can sort of make a
sleepy time smoothie.
So if you think maybe you know,
right when you're feeding Sof,
maybe you give yourself a
little sleepy time smoothie,
and you get in the mood to sleep.
(laughter)
- Here's what's coming
up next on DBL. (laughs)
(exciting music)
- [Announcer] Entertainment
icons take fashion
to an outrageous new level,
at the annual Met Gala in New York.
But who came dressed as a burger?
Then sunscreen danger exposed.
The new FDA study that
might make you think twice
before slathering sunblock on this summer.
And our wedding series continues
with the most flattering looks for guests.
We've got something for
everyone, when we come back.
(inspiring music)
- I love what we get to do every day.
I like to think of it as soul food.
It's sort of fills the
place that you didn't know
that you needed to give some goodness.
I think goodness grows.
♪ We make an impact together ♪
♪ Oh ♪
(driving pop music)
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm dan from MarketPro Homebuyers,
and we wanna buy your home.
- MarketPro Homebuyers
gave us a fair offer,
and truly helped my family.
- Call us today at 301-799-7355.
- Get the deals now,
during The Great American
Tent Sale, at Sears.
Save up to 50% off summer fashions
and sandals for the family,
including kids swimwear, starting at $8.
And up to 40% off appliances,
including this Kenmore
french door refrigerator,
for $1,299.99, plus you get
$300 cash back in points
to spend anywhere in
the store over 20 weeks.
Start your shopping, during
The Great American Tent Sale,
in store or at Sears.com
to start making your
summer moments matter.
- Just a reminder that
the rockets red glare,
and the bombs bursting in air,
are brought to you this
and every fourth of July,
by Phantom Fireworks.
With state-of-the-art
showrooms nationwide.
We are America's number one destination
for brighter, louder, safer fireworks.
Phantom Fireworks, lighting up faces
in the backyards of America,
from coast to coast.
Visit fireworks.com for
a location near you.
- To the explorers,
the hands-in-the-sand, wide-eyed
wanderers of the world.
The water is calling.
Where will it take you?
Discover the pull at
the National Aquarium.
By tickets at aqua.org.
(drumming beat music)
- Nike fire.