- [Narrator] Live life comfortably.
(energetic music)
- [Narrator] Lara Logan investigates
the ongoing border
crisis, tonight at five.
- [Announcer] It's LIVE
with Kelly and Ryan.
Today, we catch up with Kate Hudson
and Mr. Worldwide, Pitbull.
Plus, straight from the big screen,
actor Winston Duke.
And, a performance from Daughtry.
All next, on LIVE.
And now...
Here are Kelly Ripa, and Ryan Seacrest.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
- Yep, let's go!
(man mumbles)
- Good Morning.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
Good morning.
I like that one.
"Electricity", right?
A little Dua Lipa there, and the gang.
- Hey, it is Wednesday, July 3rd, 2019.
It is my dad's birthday today!
(audience applauding and cheering)
- Happy birthday, Joe Ripa!
- Happy birthday, Joe Ripa.
It's a big one.
I'm not gonna blow
up your age.
- Does he have a
traditional celebration?
- Well, you know,
every year, he likes to
say that they do fireworks,
and they have a big cookout.
- For his birthday.
- But I'm like, that's
pretty much everybody.
- You know, that was for me.
- Yeah.
- That was for me, that
whole thing up in the sky.
Well, my greatest memory of your father
is he and I laying on a chaise lounge,
in The Bahamas together,
with him giving me life
advice and guidance,
and asking if I wanted
representation, by him,
to negotiate my next deal.
(audience laughing)
He was gonna be my union member.
- It was the sweet, (stammers)--
- [Gelman] He was trying to unionize you.
- He was (stammers)
unionize us.
- Yeah.
- He was telling us that
we needed to unionize.
And I said, We are in a union, Dad.
Believe it or not, we are in a union.
- I felt like he accepted
me in that moment.
- He really did.
The two of you were--
- Right. (laughs)
- I have pictures of that,
and they're some of my favorite memories.
Because, you two are so funny together.
The two of you,
- It was--
- Because, you take on
my dad's personality
when you talk to my dad.
(audience laughs)
- I became...
- Yeah.
- I became stern.
- I became...
My voice got deeper.
- Yeah.
(audience laughs)
- I find when I talk to athletes, too,
I do the same thing.
- Right.
- Like I, "So how was the game?"
- Yeah.
(audience laughs)
And you always say to my dad,
"Joe Ripa."
- Joe Ripa.
- Yeah, it's like you puff up,
and then you call him both names--
- Joe Ripa.
- Which most people do.
Most people call me both names.
- Kelly Ripa.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, well, it's like one.
I mean, come on,
Kelly Ripa.
- It's one name.
- There's Kelly Ripa.
There's Kelly Ripa.
Kelly Ripa through the park.
- But, I mean, before this show,
I'm going back to high school.
- Keripa?
- I was both names.
- Well--
- Keripa.
(audience laughs)
Listen, if you're--
- You're making me more
of a sound than... (laughs)
- (laughs) Well, happy
Fourth of July, Keripa.
- Thank you.
- I was reading this about, you know,
thank you for tuning in in the morning.
I don't know what your
morning routines are,
your morning habits are,
but there's a whole article on
surprising morning habits that
can give you more anxiety.
And, just by reading it,
I got more anxiety.
- Right, of course.
(audience laughs)
You saying the word anxiety
- Gives you--
- Gave me anxiety.
- Cortisols releasing right now,
isn't it?
Right now, yeah.
- Is cortisol releasing into your system?
- Yeah.
- Well let it out.
- That's why I stopped wearing
pants with a zipper.
(audience laughs)
Yeah, can't do it.
- That's the reason?
- That's the reason.
- Oh!
- I can't do it.
I can't work in live TV,
and have a waistband.
(laughing)
No waist anymore.
I'm like, forget it.
The cortisol spikes,
it's not gonna affect me
- Well, listen--
- 'Cause my dress is just gonna widen.
- Do you jump--
They say it's bad for you
to jump right outta bed.
Like to get right outta bed is bad.
It causes a spike in all of that.
- Well.
- Do you jump right out?
Or do you lay there for,
I lay there and moan for a minute.
(audience laughs)
- I usually set snooze.
I do one snooze, but--
- I find it to be painful.
- The snooze?
- Yeah.
'Cause I know it's coming
and I can't, you know,
it's like that anxiety?
- Yeah, but I like that.
It's like (stammers) I hit snooze,
but the whole time,
I'm quasi-awake,
and knowing that--
- It's coming?
But see, that gives me anxiety,
knowing it's coming.
- I just burped, and that gave me anxiety.
- By the way...
(audience laughs)
Can I say, that garlic smells great.
- Oh, no, it's not.
It's not garlic.
- No, I know.
(laughs) I know it's not garlic.
Doing household chores...
Gives you anxiety, so quit.
- Wait, that gives you anxiety?
Household chores?
- Yeah.
- Knowing you have--
- At the start of your day,
at the start of,
this is all at the beginning
of the day.
- Oh, they're saying don't do
it at the start of the day.
- Yeah, don't do it at the
beginning of the day.
Don't look at your work email
the second you get outta bed.
Don't look at your to-do list.
Don't skip breakfast.
- I mean, I do all of that.
- I know, right?
- I do every--
- But, you get to
wear a dress, and it's all fine.
- Well, I mean,
they make it look fine
- There's no waist band.
- I liken myself to a
Westminster show dog.
Yeah, it looks very fluffy on the outside.
But, on the inside,
it's like, is this done yet?
(laughing)
Can we just...
Can you please put me back in my cage?
I just wanna...
I don't wanna stand before
the judges right now.
- I do find looking at the phone,
I try not to do it first thing.
Which is hard sometimes,
because you're turning off your alarm,
and then all this
stuff is there.
- I have to look at it,
because usually he's either texted me,
or you've texted me over
some thing that's happened
in the middle of the night.
- Some inane thing.
- Yeah, some thing
that has happened.
- That's true.
- So I have to check it
first thing in the morning.
You know, it's not just my
dad's birthday today, okay?
I want you to know it's also
another national holiday.
- What is that?
- A special day.
- And, I believe it could
become an international holiday,
if we get it trending here.
It is National Compliment Your Mirror Day.
- [Gelman] Oh, my goodness!
- Yes.
Yes.
(laughing)
(applause)
Lady in the front row's like,
no, it is not.
Oh, yes, it is.
You wanna know how it works?
Watch this.
- Okay.
- Kay, you hold this.
- I'm not complimenting
a picture of me.
- You hold it.
- Here.
- Gelman, you wanna do it too?
And, I'll read?
- Sure, I can do it, yeah.
- Yes.
You stand next to Ryan.
I wanna see who does--
- Gelman celebrates
this every day.
- Oh, I know!
Trust me, I know.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Here's what you do, everybody.
Stand in front of your mirror
- Oh God.
- With your eyes closed.
That's the key.
- That's the key.
Close your eyes.
- Turns the lights off.
- Yeah.
(clears throat)
Put a big smile on your face.
Eyes closed, big smile.
Now, open your eyes.
- No!
(audience laughs)
I don't wanna see it, no.
- Wow, isn't the picture of the person
in the mirror absolutely stunning?
- Oh, yes!
(audience laughs)
- Who's making love to themself over here?
What is going on?
- Don't let this special
holiday be overshadowed
by the 4th of July.
- No!
I'm feeling very positive.
- I have to tell you, I actually--
- Make sure you compliment your mirror
for displaying the beautiful person...
- Oh, God.
- Thank you, mirror!
What a great mirror you are!
(laughing)
- Gag, gag, gag.
- You're my favorite mirror.
You're a good mirror.
- Okay, Gelman.
- All right, goodbye.
- Thank you, Gelman.
(audience applauding and cheering)
- I was reading this article
about smartphones at the gym.
I guess, if you go to
the gym and work out,
the gyms want you to post
that you're working out at the gym.
Because, they get good free
publicity, and marketing.
- Well, especially your gym
where all the models go.
- Woo!
- (laughs) Yeah.
- That's why--
- It looks like a
Victoria Secret shoot every time.
I'm like, oh, there's Ryan
at his gym again.
- Hey, look, it's the only gym
that has enough weight for me.
- [Gelman] Oh, woo!
(laughing)
Three pounders?
- Yeah, I have the little
pink ones you hold.
(audience laughing)
- Do they make sounds?
- Yeah, they make shaker sounds.
- They make sounds.
- To some Daddy Yankee music.
- Ooh wee
- But this article is about gym etiquette.
They say, don't Face-time or
Skype in front of other people.
No photos in the locker room.
- Oh, yeah, naw.
- No.
(laughing)
Wait until after a class
to ask the instructor for the selfie.
Now, what I find...
People do in the gym,
is they take their phone,
- Yeah.
- And they set it up over here,
you know?
- Yeah.
And, they record.
- Then, they go over
here to do curls,
- Right.
- And then, you walk through
their shot and (scoffs).
- Yeah, well, guess what?
- I mean, what?
- Guess what?
That's exactly their problem,
not your problem.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Because that is a, (stammers) the floor,
this is gonna sound like a
shock to all the millennials,
the floor is for a walking.
(audience laughs)
- Well, the good--
- It's not an imaginary tripod
for you to lean your cellphone,
so you can have a selfie,
so you can remember,
so you can be nostalgic in real time.
(audience laughs)
Right?
- Listen, these are the people
that are celebrating the
mirror day all day today.
So, they won't be at the gym.
- That's right.
(audience laughs)
That's right, they're taking a
day off today.
- They're taking the day off
to just celebrate themselves, again.
- Yes, that is true.
- Shall we, are we?
- Sure, we could do that.
I mean, I do have my study on insomnia.
- [Gelman] Oh!
- Do it.
- You wanna know why we're so,
why we're such insomniacs?
- Why are we such insomniacs?
- Embarrassing thoughts
keep us awake at night.
(laughing)
- I think just thoughts.
Like a sum of all thoughts
keep me awake.
- Well, that's what I said.
- Like everything happens.
- I was like thoughts
keep me awake at night.
Not necessarily embarrassing
thoughts because--
- Just like a flow.
- I am a human experiment,
that you cannot die from embarrassment.
- You are, that's correct.
- I'm still here, right.
- You are good on that.
- But...
They are saying that like,
daily blunders can creep into
the margins of our brain.
And so, we fall asleep,
but suddenly, the thought
of something mortifying
that happened during the day creeps in.
- It does.
- Right.
- It does but there's 40
other thoughts happening
at the same time.
- Right.
- So one by one, shh,
I try and quiet them.
- Right.
- Shh, then the alarm goes off.
It's morning (murmurs).
I'm still trying to quiet them.
- You're trying to quiet that?
- I'm trying to quiet.
- Yeah.
- You know, I mean, I
try to quiet the thought.
It's hard to do sometimes.
- I always worry that I've
hurt somebody's feelings
and that creeps back to me, you know?
You know my sense of humor.
Sometimes I'll...
- Yeah.
- I'll use some of my best stuff
on people I don't know that well,
and they're like.
- And they don't, right.
- And I go, no, I'm kidding.
See, that's my...
- That's my personality.
(audience laughs)
- And then, that creeps in at night.
And I go, oh, I don't think
so and so got my humor
at the funeral tonight.
(laughing)
Right?
- No, I've never had that happen.
Today, on the show?
- Yeah, we have a great show.
- Kate Hudson is here.
- Yeah.
- Woo!
- You ready for Kate Hudson?
(audience cheering and applauding)
- Pitbull is also here!
- Winston Duke is here.
- Mr. Worldwide!
Yeah, and a performance by Daughtry.
- Now, tomorrow is the 4th of July.
And, all week long,
we're playing a special audience edition
of Stump the Hosts.
Where an audience member shares
a summer-themed truth or lie,
and we have to figure which one is true.
- Yeah, if they stump us,
they get a Kelly and Ryan mug,
and a $1,200 appliance
package from Cuisinart.
- Woo!
- That's right.
(audience cheering and applauding)
- Alright.
- So far this week, we have not,
that's right, not been stumped.
- Wow!
- But the weeks is.
- It's still young.
- The week is young.
Cover your mug, Kelly.
- Okay.
- All right.
- It's time for Stump the
Hosts Audience Edition!
(audience cheering and applauding)
♪ Pump up the jam ♪
♪ Pump it up ♪
♪ While your feet are stompin' ♪
♪ And the jam is pumpin' ♪
♪ Look ahead, the crowd is jumpin' ♪
♪ Pump it up a little more ♪
♪ Get the party goin' on the dance floor ♪
♪ See, 'cause that's
where the party's at ♪
♪ And you'd find out if you do that ♪
(Ryan murmurs)
There she is.
♪ Get your booty on the floor tonight ♪
- You know her, you love
her as Jessica Jackson,
from Phoenix, Arizona.
Jessica, happy 4th!
- Woo!
- Nice.
- [Ryan] Good to have you with us.
- That's the other Jessie J.
(laughing)
- So, we're gonna meet the
studio audience member now, right?
- Yeah, that's right.
Let's meet our participant
from Knoxville, Tennessee.
Where is Christie Bruce?
- Woo!
- Christie Bruce!
(audience applauding and cheering)
- Hi!
- Woo!
- Hi, Christie!
- Hey, adorable.
- Sweet girl.
- Oh, you are beautiful!
- Hi.
- Hi!
- How you doin'?
- I'm great.
How are you doin'?
- Nice to see you.
It's a pleasure.
- I've got to tell you,
Christie Bruce, you
have an absolute joyful,
joyful sunshine face.
- Oh, thank you.
- You do.
- You really do.
You have a smile that makes me smile.
- Well, good, I'm glad.
- Yeah, that's good.
- So, you should win bonus points.
- We hope so.
- Yes!
- Just for that.
- Bonus points, yes!
- So, you're gonna give us two statements.
- Okay.
- Alright?
- Alright.
- And we're gonna try
and guess which is true.
If you stump us, you win.
- Okay.
Alright, this is gonna be hard.
- Okay, all right, here we go.
The first lie or, no, the
first truth or lie is,
growing up, we had a houseboat.
On Norris Lake, in Knoxville, Tennessee.
My family had a boat,
and we would all ski.
We would all do it.
There would four of us, sometimes five.
We would all line up,
and we would do pyramids.
- Behind the houseboat?
- Behind the house,
well, not the houseboat,
'cause we had a boat,
but we kinda just--
- So you had a houseboat,
and a ski boat.
- Right, so we would go out,
and we would ski out,
and sometimes we would compete.
We were the McMichaels.
We would travel, and
do local competitions.
- [Ryan] All right, what's the second one?
Then, we'll start asking questions.
- The second one is
I was Miss Tiny Tot of Tennessee.
And, on 4th of July,
I would do the 4th of July parade,
and sit on the convertible,
and wave to the crowd.
- Oh, wave.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
Let me see your parade wave.
- Well, it was bad,
- Okay.
- Because, my mom told me
I would wave like this to everybody
and they're like, no, no,
no, you got to give it.
You got to give it good.
- You really have
to use the whole arm.
- And, how old were you
when you were Miss Tiny Tot?
- I was seven.
- Seven.
- Is Miss Tiny Tot--
- I don't care.
- A real thing?
- I want her to be Miss
Tiny Tot because...
I think you're Miss
Tiny Tot on this show!
- Is there a Miss Tiny Tot
circuit out there?
- Miss Tiny Tot!
- It is very rare that I am
bigger than somebody.
- I am tiny, yes, yes!
So, you are our Miss Tiny Tot.
- What does the audience
have to say about this?
- Oh!
- Oh, wow!
- I mean, they really believe
you have all those boats.
- But, I want her to be Miss--
Oh, what is going on right now?
- It's staying 80/20.
- I wanna believe that she.
- Do you wanna go with it, Kel?
- [Woman] Go with what you--
- You know, it's your father's birthday.
- Alright, lock it in.
- You go with what you want.
- Uh-uh.
(Kelly laughs)
I'm not gonna say a word.
- Alright, let's just say that,
I'll go with the audience,
and say that she was part
of a water skiing troop.
- Is that true?
- No, I was Miss Tiny of Tennessee.
(audience applauding and cheering)
You wanted me to be Miss
Tiny Tot, and I was!
I was Miss Leprechaun, too.
- You were?
- Oh, yeah.
I had multiple titles.
- Oh, my gosh!
- You are amazing.
- She's a multiple-title winner!
- Geez, she's going down in history,
ladies and gentlemen.
- Alright!
- So now, you help a member
of our studio audience
receive a $500 gift card from Club Monaco.
- Alright, so get out your
tickets.
- So there you go.
- Can I pick one of my friends?
- Yeah, if you can find their number,
you can pick one of your friends.
- Okay.
- Just, remember, no looking.
- I'm looking.
- There we go, no looking.
- I'm looking, Christy
Vaughny, I'm looking.
I'm just kidding.
(laughing)
Let's see here, 125.
- 125.
- 125, there you go.
- Alright.
- Right over there in the corner.
- [Christie] Thank you all so much.
That was so fun.
- Christie, so nice to meet you.
- You, too.
You're a blast.
(lips smacking)
- We'll be right back with Kate Hudson.
- [Announcer] Still ahead on LIVE,
a performance by Daughtry.
Actor, Winston Duke.
Pitbull.
And, coming up next, Kate Hudson.
- [Narrator] You know
July 4th is a great time
for a backyard barbecue.
Lowe's helps you do it right
with savings like $9 off
a twin pack of Kingsford
Charcoal, now $14.88.
And, spruce up your landscape
before guests arrive.
With five packs of mulch for $10.
Do it right for less, start with Lowe's.
(dog howls)
- [Narrator] Dogs have evolved,
but their nutritional
needs remain instinctual.
That's why there's
Purina One True Instinct.
High protein for strong muscles.
A different breed of natural nutrition,
Purina One True Instinct.
Also in grain-free for dogs, and cats.
- [Narrator] Brushing only
reaches 25% of your mouth.
Listerine cleans virtually 100%.
Helping to prevent gum
disease, and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%.
(water spraying)
Always go for 100.
Bring out the bold.
♪ Don't give it up ♪
♪ I want it all ♪
♪ 'Cause there's nothing
like this feeling, baby ♪
♪ Now that I've found you ♪
- [Narrator] ABC7's on your side
this Capital 4th.
With live coverage of the fireworks,
the President, and the protests.
All day, on ABC7.
WJLA 24/7 News.
And, wherever you go,
streaming on the ABC 7 News app.
- Are you looking for a
hassle-free, simple way
to sell your home as is?
It doesn't matter if you're
downsizing your home,
have fallen behind in
repairs, or your mortgage.
Get an offer on your home
in as little as 10 minutes
with House Buyers of America.
We buy houses directly.
There's no middle-men, no commissions.
There's no need to deal
with real estate agents,
repairs, inspections, and renovations.
Give us a call today.
We're A+ rated with the
Better Business Bureau.
House Buyers Of America.
Real estate made real easy.
- [Narrator] Storm Watch 7.
Seven Strong.
On a mission.
- Knowing where the threat is.
Knowing how it's going to impact you.
That makes all the difference.
Storm Watch 7, seven strong,
and always on your side.
- She's a successful actress,
a best selling author,
a clothing entrepreneur,
and one of the most
lovable people we know.
Please welcome back to
the show, Kate Hudson.
(applause and cheering)
(upbeat music)
- Good to see you.
- You look so pretty!
- Thanks.
- It's so funny,
I saw that dress hanging backstage,
- Yes.
And, I was like oh my gosh.
- I made it.
- I thought that was for me.
(laughter)
- She can get you one.
- You can have it.
I'll get you one.
- Yeah.
- It's very--
- You know, it's made
out of organic cotton.
- No kidding.
- Yeah.
- So pretty.
- I'm excited to talk about it.
But, first I wanna say that...
I would, you took my job.
I would love to be in a bikini,
playing cards.
- Oh really.
- Well, you could be.
- I love a fast car,
and I love a bikini.
- Yeah, listen--
- Do you remember the White Snake video,
where they were dancing
- Yes, yes.
- On that--
- Yeah, of course.
- That could be us on the hood.
- Totally into it.
- Let's, okay.
I smell a tank-piece.
- Totally down.
- I smell it, hey Gelman.
We're just bookin' the
show, left and right.
So, you are a mom of...
Three now!
- Three.
- Three, yeah.
Or, five--
(eruptive applause)
I say 500.
It's like,
- 500.
- It feels like
I have 500 kids.
That's what it feels like.
- Well, you go from
man-to-man defense, to zone-defense.
- Yeah.
- Woo.
- And, I don't know what that means.
It just seems like it
(mumbles) up a lot.
- Oh my God.
Everyone's like, how are you?
And I'm like, exhausted.
I'm so tired.
- How old, is this six months?
The latest addition?
- Ope, she's six months.
Yesterday.
- Oh, so cute!
- Oh my gosh
- Look at her
little thighs.
- That's--
- [Kate] Oh my God, you guys.
I'm out of my mind.
- Do you ever,
do you chew on her legs?
Do you chew on her?
- I chew on everything.
- Mhm.
- (stammers) I mean,
we're all out of our minds
with Rani.
- Yeah.
- She's so cute.
- I love your copper
pans though, those are nice.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
- Copper pans?
You noticed pans?
- I have copper pans.
- Yeah, she has beautiful
copper pans.
- I actually collect copper.
- Oh, you do?
- Yeah.
- Oh well, see.
- And, I engrave them,
and everything.
- Look at that.
- [Kate] Yeah.
- That is so cute.
- It's so funny,
I was so busy looking at the,
I was like, copper pans?
(Kate laughs)
- Oh, yeah.
- Ryan's like,
nice copper pans.
- Yeah.
I'm installing a kitchen right now.
- Are her big brother's involved?
Or, are they at the
place where they're like,
oh that's, you know,
that's a diaper?
- Ryder's 15.
- Yeah.
- Which is crazy.
- I mean it's like,
- That's insane.
- I mean, he's almost (stammers),
getting up to six-feet.
And, he's such a great boy.
- He's a man.
- Young man.
- Yeah.
(sarcastic cries)
- (laughs) It's okay.
- But, the other day we were--
- I do it all the time.
- I know, I'm like,
what is it?
He's so old.
But no, the other day,
we went to breakfast,
and I was juggling a million things.
And, I think it's like,
you know, really wise to
go alone, with three kids.
You know, it's like hey,
let's go to breakfast, kids.
And, the next thing you know,
I'm not eating,
I'm juggling everything,
and I go to Ryder,
Ryder, just take Rani.
And, I went to go get
my food at the buffet,
and I looked over,
and here's this young
man holding his sis--
It was the craziest
image to me.
- Yeah.
- And, I just thought,
life is really weird.
- And, it goes fast.
- It's so fa--
Yeah, but I was like 12 when I--
I mean--
- You were 12 when--
- Yeah, in terms of like,
a Hollywood actress.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- I say, in terms
of a Hollywood actress,
I was like a teen-mom.
I mean, that's, you know.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, me and Reese were like teen-moms.
- Yeah, that's true.
- You know, it's like,
we had kids really,
super young.
- But you...
I mean, just from your posts,
you don't let being a busy
mom not have you have fun.
Like, you still like really--
- Hold on...
- Yeah.
(laughing)
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- Like, you still are you.
- But, don't you think you
learn that from your family?
Like, your family...
- Is--
- When I look at your family,
it's with admiration and envy,
'cause you all seem like you're having fun
all the time.
- All the time.
- Yeah, my parents left us
to have fun all the time.
It was like, where are you going?
They're like, we're going to Tahiti!
(laughing)
Okay.
- See you in two weeks!
- Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, we do.
We have fun.
I mean, I make sure that
- You embrace it.
- You know, kids are good,
and that I take time to
you know, let out some steam.
- To enjoy.
- Yeah.
- Although, lately it's
been hard, 'cause I'm
still breast feeding.
I gotta be honest.
- Yeah.
- It's like, my 40th is coming up,
and I keep saying,
(stammers) I deserve a
really good hangover.
- Yes.
- And, it's gonna happen.
- Listen, I wanna give
you a birthday present.
I will watch your children
so you can go tie one on.
I will do the whole--
- And, I'll go...
I'll go tie one on with you.
- That's good, perfect!
- I will take care,
I will take care of your babies.
I'm very responsible.
So now, there's (stammers).
- Break it down.
- Musicians in your family.
You're very musical.
- I love to sing.
- Yeah.
- And, I play piano.
- I didn't know that.
- Yeah, but it's like,
I keep forgetting I can't
swear on these shows.
I almost went there.
I'm not very good at it.
I can write on the piano,
but I can't like sit down,
and read music,
- Wow.
- And be like, you know.
(Kelly mumbles)
- Yeah.
- Why don't you
release a single?
- I have a movie coming out.
I think it's gonna be in the Fall,
that's a musical that Sia directed.
- Oh.
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah, it's the first time I've actually
sang contemporary music.
That's really exciting.
And, I think after that,
I'll probably even just (stammers).
I feel like it's one of those things
I have to do at some point.
I just have to put something out there.
- Listen--
- I don't care what it does--
- You know people that work on the radio.
- Oh yeah, that's right.
- Yeah.
- Oh, that guy.
- I tell ya' how
to make it a hit.
- Yeah?
- Collaborate with DJ Khalid.
- Right.
- That's right.
- That's all you gotta do.
Just get DJ Khalid, Kate Hudson--
- Or, Mr. WorldWide.
- Or, Mr. WorldWide!
- Mr. WorldWide.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I got it.
You know what though?
I have to say,
I miss bands.
I really do.
Like, my son's really musical.
Bing is insane--
(stammers) Almost...
He drums.
I can't get him out of his
drumming room.
- That's great.
- He's now started playing keyboard,
and he's never had a piano--
(Kelly murmurs)
Oh yeah, he's not even
eight years old.
- He's got it in the genes.
- It's kind of crazy.
And, I just thought...
Oh, he's gonna get in a band,
and like, ugh,
it's gonna be tough (laughs).
- Yeah, yeah.
He's gonna tour the world.
- It's gonna be a hard life.
- No, but it's an exciting life.
Don't you think?
- Being (stammers) a touring musician?
(sighs)
- Well, she was--
- Yeah, but I mean--
- You have some
experience with that.
- I mean, it's a lot of work.
You know?
- Yeah.
- And, it's amazing when you love it.
But, it's a whole different like--
Jazz Cats.
- Oh.
- Like, all the people
that I'm really close to,
and touring musicians
who still spend 200 days
of the year on the road.
- On the road.
- But, I'm thinking about
your parents, right.
They were probably like,
oh gosh, not acting.
It's such a,
like an unstable career, right?
If you have a calling for it.
- Yeah, do it.
- Imagine if your mom said to you,
Kate listen, anything but acting.
- Yeah.
- Right?
- That would have been very, yeah.
It would have been hard--
- But, you're entrepreneuring.
I mean, you've got all of these
fashion brands--
- I just can't stop working.
- Great!
- I love to work, and--
- [Kelly] Well, you're good at it.
- I've always wanted to design clothes.
- What's Happy By Nature?
- So, Happy By Nature is my first like,
ready-to-wear fashion line.
- It's fantastic.
I'm so happy for you.
- Thank you,
I'm really excited.
I'm excited.
It's one of those things I've been
working really hard on it.
I feel like every time I
put my name to anything,
whether I'm endorsing it,
or banking it, like this.
- Right.
- I have to believe in it.
It has to be something
that I feel is important.
And so, this is a very eco-friendly line,
and the fashion industry
is like the worst,
number two worst carbon
footprint of all industries.
And, I really feel like
the fashion industry
needs to look at how
they're making things,
and start changing the
way that they do stuff.
And, I feel like we--
(audience applauds)
Yeah.
- Well--
- And, I feel like we're gonna really,
hopefully make an impact there.
- Well, you're a nature girl.
So, you grew up...
- Yeah.
- In nature, really.
- I mean--
- In Brentwood.
- In Brent--
- No, but she also, Colorado.
- No.
- She's a Colorado girl.
- Colorado.
- Oh, Colorado, okay.
- And then, Brentwood.
- Then Brentwood.
- [Kelly] Yeah.
(laughing)
(Kelly and Ryan stammer)
- There's a median of grass.
- Yeah, yeah.
- This is beautiful.
- Thank you.
- So, you can go to our
website for more information
about Kate's fashion line,
Happy By Nature.
(applause and cheering)
Great to see you.
- [Announcer] Still ahead, on Live,
we'll talk with Pitbull.
♪ Excuse me, excuse me ♪
- I remember putting on a brave face
to hide my symptoms of depression.
I was on an anti-depressant,
but I still had depression symptoms.
It was tough getting through the day,
hiding how I really felt.
Something had to change.
So, I talked to my doctor, for real.
No more saying oh, I'm fine.
This time, I spoke up about
living behind the mask.
And, he told me about Rexulti.
He said that Rexulti,
when added to an anti-depressant,
has been proven to help
reduce symptoms of depression.
Without giving up the progress
I may have made on my anti-depressant.
- [Narrator] Rexulti is not for everyone.
Call your doctor about
unusual changes in behavior,
worsening depression,
or thoughts of suicide.
Anti-depressants can increase
these in those 24, and younger.
Elderly dementia patients taking Rexulti
have an increased risk of death or stroke.
Call your doctor if you have high-fever,
stiff muscles, and confusion,
to address a possible
life-threatening condition.
Or, if you have uncontrollable
muscle movements,
as these may be permanent.
Rexulti has been shown to increase
blood-sugar in some people.
Other risks are increased
cholesterol, weight gain,
unusual urges or compulsive behaviors,
decreased white blood-cells,
which can be serious,
dizziness on standing,
seizures, trouble swallowing,
and impaired judgment or motor skills.
- It was time to make a change.
That's why I asked my
doctor about adding Rexulti.
- [Narrator] Feel better
about facing the world.
Pay $0 for your first
Rexulti prescription.
Details at rexulti.com.
- [Narrator] It's Regency
Furniture's July 4th celebration!
And, everything's on sale!
When Regency cuts
furniture prices this low,
you will save 50%!
Plus, this week, get free delivery,
and Regency pays your sales tax.
Save on the biggest July 4th celebration.
Now, at Regency Furniture.
- [Narrator] ABC7's on your
side, this capital 4th.
With live coverage of the fireworks,
the president, and the protests.
All day, On ABC7.
WJLA 24/7 News.
And, wherever you go,
streaming on the ABC7 News app.
(gentle music)
- [Narrator] At Value City Furniture,
we know great moments
deserve great furniture.
(laughter)
Hurry in now, to the 4th of July sale,
and save 10%-30% off, store-wide.
No minimum purchase required.
Or, for a limited time,
enjoy 48 months special financing.
Now, on purchases of just $999 or more.
With payments starting
as low as $21 a month.
Get the savings you want
during the 4th of July sale.
Going on now,
at Value City Furniture.
♪ Yeah, que no pare la fiesta ♪
♪ Don't stop the party ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, ♪
♪ Que no pare la fiesta ♪
♪ Don't stop the party ♪
- Oh yeah, you and me both.
- Right?
- He is a Grammy winning,
international super-star.
Mr. 305, Mr. WorldWide.
Please welcome Pitbull.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
- Got 'em.
Got 'em, got 'em, got 'em, got 'em.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
- Hi!
(Pitbull murmurs)
How are you?
- Yes, sir.
- Good to see you, baby.
- Love it.
I mean, the fans.
(laughing)
The fans go nuts.
- Yeah.
- Armando fans are here.
- (mumbles) Yee-ooh!
(audience applauding and cheering)
I think I got the wrong glasses on.
- Oh yeah, yeah.
- Are these your glasses?
- Oh my gosh.
I know, I'm sorry.
You look--
- Studious.
- But, I can see everybody
really close right now.
(laughing)
- Sorry about that.
Sorry (laughs).
- So listen...
- Boom, there we go.
- To go back for people
who don't know your story.
- Yeah.
- It is an incredible story.
- Been very blessed, thank God.
(knocking)
Thanks for the fans.
I wouldn't be here without y'all.
- I wanna talk about--
(audience applauding and cheering)
The challenges at the beginning for you,
and what you did to overcome,
to get to be who you are now.
- Well, I mean...
Oof..
A lot of different obstacles,
but I think that,
that's what makes the journey fun.
You know, from nothing to something.
A whole lot of no's.
- Yeah.
- That's for sure.
And, a whole lot of you can't,
you won't, you never will,
don't, you're crazy,
how dare you, impossible.
And then, I flipped every word,
by the way.
- Yeah.
- So, my daughter taught me,
in the word impossible, is possible.
- Yeah.
- Right?
And, I took the word can't, is can.
- Yeah.
- Won't, is won.
- Yes.
- Don't, is do.
- And, that's exactly
what we doin' with our career.
- It's really--
- 20 years in the game, baby.
- 20 years too.
- Yeah.
- Isn't that great?
- Amazing.
- You got your first record
deal from a rap battle.
- Yeah, it was a rap battle against,
back in the day,
was a crew called "The Ruff Ryders".
A guy named DMX
- Yes, of course.
- Was a part of it.
- Yeah.
- I was very, I was
invited to his video shoot,
and I battled this guy named Drag-on,
at the video shoot,
Swizz Beatz was there.
- Mhm.
- And, Swizz Beatz told me
I'll give you three rounds with the Drag--
'Cause, he's a dragon, you know.
He's gonna burn you.
I said man, I'm just happy to be here.
- [Kelly] Right.
(laughing)
- I had home-court advantage.
It was in Miami.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
And, I flipped a couple words
in Spanish here and there.
Called out a couple neighborhoods.
It worked out, you know?
And, we won (laughs).
- Oh my gosh, that's great.
- Yeah.
- And, that's where it all started?
- Yup.
You know what's crazy,
is that's on video.
And the footage,
you can't find it anywhere.
- Really?
- Crazy enough, yeah.
There's a guy out there,
Jamie, if you're looking at this,
I know you still got
that footage (mumbles).
- [Kelly] Jamie!
- Let's go, cough it up.
- You need to show
the world that, Jamie.
- I would love to see that.
- Oh, you will.
You will.
- Yeah.
- Now that I said that, you'll see it.
It'll get out, one way or another.
- And also, when you were growing up,
- Yeah.
- Your mom would put on
tapes of Tony Robbins
- Yup.
- In the car, right?
- So, I lived in a neighborhood
called Carol City, in Miami.
- Yeah.
- And...
I was not trying to
listen to Tony Robbins.
And, whenever my mom
could take me to school,
it was an '82 Pinto that she
would take me to school in,
and she said,
she put Tony on.
I wanted to hear like,
2 Live Crew, and Poison Clan.
(laughing)
So, one day I go to change the radio to,
you know, to my music,
and she's like, (smack), bam.
She said, do you pay for this car?
I said, no.
She said, well then don't touch my radio.
(laughing)
- And so, you were
listening to Tony Robbins?
- So, subliminally, I
started listening to Tony,
and all it took was one story.
Which was a story about Colonel Sander's,
and how it took him 1,007 no's
before he could sell his recipe.
And, I thought about it like,
man it's hard to get one no out of my mom.
I go, man, imagine 1,007 of 'em.
So, the word no became yes.
You know, I welcome failure.
I welcome the slip.
I welcome the fall.
I welcome the no.
I mean, you guys know.
- Yeah, of course.
- You know, and failure's
the mother of all success.
And, I've learned that
through out the game.
Every record that has been
huge for us around the world,
thanks to you guys,
every record exec said,
mmm not gonna work.
So, the minute that they
don't say that's a hit,
I'm like, ope, throw that out the window.
(Ryan mumbles)
- We get it.
- Yes.
(laughing)
It's true.
- Yeah, yeah.
- It's true.
I mean, you've had...
It's like...
I had the fortunate opportunity
to play Pitbull's music
every single day.
- Right, I put you on
one of the records.
- He put me in a lyric.
- Yeah.
- I was so excited.
- Wait, wait, wait,
what lyric?
- It says...
It was...
Give me everything...
- Which was a huge (mumbles)
- Where I said
my family's from Cuba,
but I'm an American idol,
getting money like Seacrest.
- [Kelly] Oh, yes!
(laughing)
(audience applauding and cheering)
- More with Pitbull.
How he became an ugly dog, after this.
Stay with us.
- Yee-ooh!
- [Announcer] Tomorrow, on Live.
The cast of "Stranger Things".
(audience applauding and cheering)
- [Narrator] Today,
people across the nation
are experiencing the benefits
of joining PENFED Credit Union.
With the PENFED car buying service,
they're finding the right
car at a better price.
And, everyone is welcome to apply.
Join today, at PENFED.org.
- With COX, you get everything you
wanna watch in one place,
using the voice remote.
- Show me action.
(ding)
- Even a ninny like me can figure it out.
(distant clacking)
With streaming apps, you miss live events,
and waste time searching for shows.
- Not this one, that one.
- It's clear that COX
is the better choice.
Just like it's clear that
the teleprompter guys thinks
I'm a boo-boo-head who
steals parking spots.
(adventurous music)
- [Narrator] Get live TV, great apps,
and On Demand, from COX.
Starting at $79.99 a month.
- [Narrator] Here's
three-time gold medalist,
Misty May-Treanor.
For Vein Clinics of America.
- I was surprised to
see I had vein disease.
I didn't think I was old enough.
But, I didn't wanna risk my health,
or the performance of my legs.
So, I went right to
Vein Clinics of America.
- [Narrator] For over 35 years,
Vein Clinics of America has been a leader
in the treatment of vein disease.
Varicose veins, and spider veins,
are much more than an
unsightly cosmetic problem.
Often, it's a serious medical condition.
Call, or go online now,
to see if you qualify to book a
free no-obligation consult.
- [Misty] The veins they
treated are completely gone.
It's like they turned back time.
- [Narrator] All treatments are done on
an out-patient basis,
and many procedures are covered
by most insurance plans.
- I want my legs to stay
healthy, strong, and beautiful.
That's why I went to
Vein Clinics of America.
- [Narrator] Call, or go online right now,
to see if you qualify
to book your free consultation.
Vein Clinics of America,
healthy looks good.
- [Narrator] Call 1-800-593-6331.
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm Dan, from MarketPro Home Buyers,
and we wanna buy your home.
Don't make repairs, don't pay commissions,
and don't wait another day.
We'll get you the cash you need.
No agent fees, no closing costs.
We'll even help you
pack and move, for free.
For a no-obligation
offer, call 301-750-SELL.
That's 301-750-7355.
Or, visit marketprohomebuyers.com.
We buy houses as-is, on your schedule.
Call today.
- [Narrator] With the
PENFED car buying service,
from PENFED Credit Union,
you can get rates as
low as 2.49% APR, on used vehicles.
And, everyone is welcome to apply.
Visit PENFED.org.
♪ PENFED's got great rates for everyone ♪
- You call that a dog?
(growling)
It's alright guys.
Slick Dog's got this.
♪ Pan-pan-ameri-- ♪
♪ Bon, Bon, Bon, Bon, ♪
♪ Yo quiero estar contigo ♪
- What are you doing?
- Having fun.
Getting crazy.
Getting loose.
♪ Bon, bon, bon ♪
Go!
I'll stall him.
Go, go, go!
(laughing)
(applause and cheering)
- That's great.
- Bon, bon, bon, bon
- Something for the parents.
- Yeah.
- Little something
for the parents.
- Yeah.
- That's a scene from "Ugly Dolls",
starring Pitbull.
- Yeah.
(audience applauding and cheering)
- You play a character named Ugly Dog.
- Yeah, you know,
the people at the studio really
thought this out thoroughly.
And, they was like,
you know, your name's Pitbull,
we want you to play this dog.
- [Kelly] Right.
(laughing)
- I was like man,
you guys are geniuses.
- With an alter-ego though.
- Yeah, but it's great.
Well you know, that's why I
brought the glasses out today.
'Cause, I'm also Slick Dog.
- Right.
- I'm Ugly dog, and
Slick Dog, in the movie.
What I love about this movie, really,
you know, why I signed up for it,
it's a perfect time,
for the perfect message,
to let everybody know,
that believe it or not,
perfection doesn't exist!
- Yeah.
- You know?
And...
(applause and cheering)
And also, flip the word ugly,
which the word ugly is
U-Gotta-Love-Yourself.
Okay?
- Aw.
(audience applauding and cheering)
- Learning a little bit today, huh?
- Yeah.
- And, especially in a society
where you got all the kids
right now on social media,
and it's all about followers and likes.
When it really should be
about leaders and unique.
That's what it--
- Yeah.
- You know, who cares?
Forget about following.
You know, be yourself.
Love yourself.
- Yeah.
- And, that's what this
movie's all about.
You got Uglyville, and Perfectville.
And, guess what?
Everybody in Uglyville,
man, they love each other,
they have fun with each other,
make fun of each other,
they enjoy each other.
Everybody in Perfectville,
they just,
you know,
- Mhm.
- Everybody does the same thing,
and they all look the same.
So, Uglyville...
I can't spoil the movie for y'all.
(laughing)
You know?
- I do like the way you,
I like the way you were
acting it out though.
- I get loose,
I have fun.
You know, we get a chance to enjoy,
and so it was a lot of fun.
Obviously, you see I'm
very excited about it.
And, they gave me a
chance to actually be me
in a cartoon character.
- It's really great.
- Yeah, it's a lot of fun.
- Have you thought about
being you in a movie?
- Well, you know,
let me tell you,
I'm Mr. WorldWide, alright?
But, Ryan...
Okay, Ryan is Mr. Non-Exclusive.
(laughing)
This man has a deal with everybody.
So I'm like, Ryan,
how can I use your attorney?
Okay?
(laughing)
So, you would understand me,
when it comes to movies,
I like to be more off-camera,
invest, and be partners in it.
- So, are you saying
- But--
- You want Ryan to star as you--
- Oh, that would be great.
- Let me see the glasses.
- There you go.
What?
Ayy, get it, get it,
get it, get it, get it!
(laughing)
(applause and cheering)
- I just wanna watch this all day.
Don't, wait...
- Oh, that was great.
- What?
- Greatest thing I've ever seen.
(laughing)
Ugly Dolls.
Make sure to check out (murmurs).
(mumbles)
- [Announcer] Friday, on Live.
Ricky Gervais.
- This July 4th...
- Things are getting strange around here.
- [Announcer] Next Live, the
boys of "Stranger Things",
house-band O.A.R,
and 4th of July games.
It's gonna be big.
- [Kelly] Like, inflatable flamingo big.
(laughing)
- My body is truly powerful.
- I have the power to lower
my blood-sugar, and A1C.
- Because, I can still
make my own insulin,
and Trulicity activates
my body to release it.
Like, it's supposed to.
- [Narrator] Trulicity is for
people with type 2 diabetes.
It's not insulin.
- [Man] I take it once a week.
It starts acting in my
body from the first dose.
- [Narrator] Trulicity isn't for people
with type 1 diabetes,
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Don't take Trulicity if
you're allergic to it,
you or your family have
medullary thyroid cancer,
or have multiple endocrine
neoplasia syndrome type 2.
Stop Trulicity, and call
your doctor right away,
if you have an allergic reaction,
a lump or swelling in your neck,
or severe stomach pain.
Serious side effects may
include pancreatitis.
Taking Trulicity with a
sulfonylureas, or insulin,
increases low blood-sugar risk.
Side effects include nausea, diarrhea,
vomiting, belly pain,
and decreased apetite.
Which lead to dehydration,
and may worsen kidney problems.
- I have it within me to lower my A1C.
- [Narrator] Ask your
doctor about Trulicity.
(Honda chime)
- [Narrator] Ger ready for clearance.
It's the Honda 4th of July sales event.
Accords on clearance.
Civics on clearance.
CR-Vs and HR-Vs on clearance.
Even the third-row Pilot is on clearance.
With features on clearance,
safety on clearance,
and selection on clearance.
Like a new Civic for just $189 a month.
Or, get a new CR-V for just $259 a month.
Don't miss the Honda
4th of July sales event.
Did we mention it was clearance?
Going on now, at your local Honda dealer.
- [Narrator] Get the deals now,
during The Great American
tent sale at Sears.
Save up to 50% off Summer fashions,
and sandals for the family.
Including kids swimwear, starting at $8.
And, up to 40% off appliances.
Including this Kenmore,
french-door refrigerator, for $1,299.99.
Plus, you get $300 cash back in points
to spend anywhere in the store,
over twenty weeks.
Start your shopping during
The Great American tent sale.
In store, or at Sears.com,
to start making your
Summer moments matter.
(applause and cheering)
- He is an award winning actor.
We know him as M'Baku,
from "Black Panther".
And now, he starts in Jordan
Peele's new thriller, "US".
Please welcome Winston Duke, everybody.
(upbeat music)
(applause and cheering)
- How are you?
- So great.
So great.
- So happy to see you.
- How are you, bro?
- Good to see you, man.
- Nice to see you!
- Oh, wonderful.
- Oh, he feels like an Oscar winner.
- He does.
Yes, you actually look like
an Oscar winner.
- From your lips,
to God's ears.
- Yes, yes.
- Well, you guys did.
You won some Oscar's.
- Yeah, we got three
Oscar's for "Black Panther".
- What a thrill.
- Yes.
- I mean, really incredible.
(applause and cheering)
And, is the sequel...
Are you working on the sequel?
Can we talk about that yet?
- Is that like your smooth
pitch to find out
- No, just trying--
what's going on?
- Just trying to figure out
if there's a sequel in the works.
- Yeah, there's a definitely
a "Black Panther 2".
- Good.
- Yeah.
- In the works.
Everything's very hush-hush with Marvel,
and Disney.
- Right.
- Around it.
- Yes.
- You know, if you're
eager for a M'Baku fix,
I'll be in the...
"The Avengers Infinity War Part 2".
- Okay, great.
- So, that's coming.
- That's coming as well.
- That is great.
- And, we understand as well,
you're celebrating all the success,
you bought a house?
- I did, I did.
- Congratulations,
happy home owner.
- Thank you, so much.
Thank you, so much.
- You know, that's what it is.
I thought you looked more burdened
than the last time I saw you.
- I think it's with all
the home renovations.
That's what it is.
You know, finding furniture that fits.
- Exactly.
- Yes, yes.
Especially 'cause I'm a big guy.
So, I'm always trying
to make the things work,
but you know,
- Yeah.
- It's all about size and scale.
- You want a sumptuous sofa.
- I like that word.
- Yes.
(laughing)
- Sumptuous.
- Yeah.
- So, you have to,
you actually are shopping
for larger than normal
couches?
- I'm not larger than normal,
it's just...
Things that fit me,
but also are in proportion to the home.
- You know, these chairs
seem to fit you well.
Maybe you'd like to--
- These work great.
- These could be great
for the dining room.
- Is this a gift?
- Yes, absolutely.
This is gift.
Gelman, we need new chairs.
(laughing)
- Are you moving anything
from your current place,
into the new place?
- Couple things.
But, really it's mainly
our first family home
in the states, you know?
- So great.
- So, it's been just a
pleasure to be able to do that.
Be the first one to purchase--
- Oh, but you have...
He has citrus.
(stammers) It's her dream to have citrus.
- My dream is to have a citrus plant
of some kind.
- Yeah.
- I live in New York City,
so that dream is probably
never going to happen.
Ryan, unbeknownst to me,
in all of the years
- I was keeping it on
- We've known each other,
- The DL, like the sequel.
- Has an orang grove.
- Oh my God.
- Okay?
He has a secret orange grove.
What do you have?
- In my secret garden.
- I have kumquats.
- Oh, no kidding!
- Kumquats, and I actually--
- The baby orange!
- You can eat them whole.
- Yes, I actually,
'cause the skin is sweet,
and the inside is sour.
- Yes.
- So, they're this like,
awesome little fruit.
- You can make a chutney
out of it.
- Ooh.
- I will make you some kumquat chutney!
- Ooh, she said chutney.
- I will make you a chutney.
Can you say it again?
- Yeah, chutney.
You can make chutney out of your kumquats.
Did you know that?
- Yes, yes.
And, I have a little present for you.
I brought you some--
- Chutney.
(Kelly gasps)
- My kumquats.
- No, you didn't!
- Yeah I did, I did.
- Are these your kumquats?
- Yes, these are my kumquats.
- I am going to chutney this.
Oh my gosh.
Really?
You just popped one right in?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- They're like,
satisfying in a poppy way.
- Yeah, yeah.
They're intense.
They're very intense.
(mumbles)
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- These are fresh.
- Yeah, they're very fresh.
(laughing)
They're from my tree.
They're from my tree,
- I can't believe
- Winston Zone.
- You brought--
(laughing)
We're gonna make you,
we're gonna make,
manufacture your chutney.
M'Baku's chutney.
(laughing)
- M'Baku's vegetarian chutney.
- Tell me that...
- I think that's
a glorious idea.
- That is a trillion
dollar idea.
- Do you...
Do you cook?
I'm gonna grab my (mumbles).
- I cook a little bit,
but because my size is
always going up and down
for each role--
- Yeah, I know the feeling.
(laughing)
- Do you have to do that a lot?
- A lot, a lot.
So, for M'Baku, I had gained about
40 pounds.
- Right.
- And then, for upcoming movie "Us",
- Jordan Peele didn't want
me to feel like a super hero.
So he was like,
if you could just eat some
burgers, or something.
So you could look just like a
dad who has responsibilities
other than going to the gym.
- Isn't that amazing?
Like, (stammers).
And, I think that this
is a uniquely male thing,
that men in their roles,
can go up and down the
scale with relative ease.
Like, just have a couple of burgers.
- Yeah, (stammers).
That was fun,
but then losing the weight is not.
- Oh, okay.
Well, I'm glad to hear you say that.
- Let's take a break.
This is your treat.
Just plant those,
and have your very own citrus tree.
- Until the first frost.
- We'll be right back,
and talk about "Us",
right after this.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Tomorrow, on Live.
A performance by O.A.R.
♪ And, I'm dreaming of you tonight ♪
- [Narrator] When
cravings come on strong...
(ding)
Be stronger.
With new Nicorette Coated Ice-mint.
Layered with flavor.
It's the first, and only,
coated nicotine lozenge.
For an amazing taste,
that outlasts your craving.
New Nicorette Ice-mint.
- [Narrator] Ashley Home Store's stars
and stripes event is going on now.
For a limited time, save up to 30%.
Get 0% interest for six whole years.
Plus, shop incredible
4th of July door-busters.
Only at America's number one
furniture and mattress store.
Ashley Home Store.
This is home.
- [Narrator] ABC7's on your
side, this capital 4th.
With live coverage of the fireworks,
the president, and the protests.
All day, On ABC7.
WJLA 24/7 News.
And, wherever you go,
streaming on the ABC7 News app.
- [Narrator] Storm Watch 7.
- Knowing where the threat is,
and knowing when it will impact you.
- Knowing Storm Watch
7 is always on alert.
Always with you.
- That makes all the difference.
- [Narrator] Storm Watch 7,
seven strong,
and always on your side.
- [Narrator] Whole house
insulated siding, $289 a month.
- Window World installs
premium siding that's
actually an energy saving wall system.
- [Narrator] Whole house insulated siding,
$289, and free estimate.
- Window World, the best for less.
(thud)
- [Narrator] Appliance shopping...
Shouldn't be painful.
Come to Bray & Scarff.
Where factory-trained appliance experts
give you the personal
attention you deserve.
And, get July 4th savings now!
With exclusive double rebates
on select kitchen packages.
Plus, this Maytag top-load washer!
With deep fill, and power
wash, for just $699.
Shop local at Bray & Scarff.
Where it doesn't cost more, to get more.
- [Man] America will let you do anything.
If you ever told me that
where I am right now,
at my age, and you gave me options.
You said you have this wife,
this house, these kids, this life.
I said, sign me up.
No doubt.
- [Woman] You don't have to be rich.
Your goal should be to be independent.
To be stable.
Know that what you're doing is
meaningful in some way.
- [Man] That is my American Dream.
- [Woman] We're the Byrd's,
from Woodbridge, Virginia,
and we've been PENFED
members for almost 20 years.
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm Dan, from MarketPro Home Buyers,
and we wanna buy your home.
- My husband and I were faced with
the decision of what to
do with my father's home.
The house required a lot of work.
That's when I found MarketPro Home Buyers.
Dan visited our home,
and within minutes,
he gave us a quote.
It was so easy.
Dan even helped pay to pack and move us.
MarketPro Home Buyers truly helped
my family when we did not know what to do.
- [Dan] Call us today, at 301-750-7355.
- [Narrator] Whole house
insulated siding, $289 a month.
- Window World installs
premium siding that's
actually an energy saving wall system.
- [Narrator] Whole house
insulated siding, $289,
and free estimate.
- Window World, the best for less.
(footsteps)
- Now, I thought I already done told y'all
to get off my property.
Okay?
So, if y'all wanna get crazy,
we can get crazy.
Now, the cops are already on they way.
(crickets chirping)
(eerie popping)
(fast footsteps)
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
(applause)
(laughing)
- Goosebumps.
- Yes!
- We are scared in thrillers like this.
- Yes.
- Yes, Jordan Peele...
I am convinced is a terrifying
person in real life.
- He actually is really just like,
a calm, smooth, unassuming guy.
You never think that
was going on up there.
- What is going on up there?
- Yeah, yeah.
That's really the thing.
- Honestly.
How does he come up with these scenarios?
- I think he's just very imaginative,
you know, his take on American cinema,
'cause I feel that's
really what "Get Out",
and this movie is doing,
is interrogating America as a culture.
With really interesting what-ifs.
- And, how many people live through this?
'Cause, it looks--
- I can't tell you that one.
- Do you survive?
- What can you tell us
about this?
- What can you tell
us about "Us"?
What can you tell us?
- What I can say is that it's deeply,
really just a family drama.
It's about a family caught
in an interesting scenario,
and they have to fight for their lives,
and they're confronted with,
essentially, their own demons.
Which are these doppelganger figures.
- Oh boy.
- That look
exactly like them.
- [Ryan] But, at least you have a bat.
- Yeah (laughs).
- I mean, look...
I want everybody to look at that photo.
Tell...
That is, I mean.
- Yeah.
- Terrifying.
- It's terrifying,
and then, you know,
being in that space,
being in that head space and that body,
was really tough to stay in.
Because, you have to go to a,
I have to go to a really
interesting place.
But, we're really well supported.
- Was it a heavy place?
- Heavy emotionally.
Because, I can't tell you anything
without giving a big
- Right, I know.
- Spoiler.
- Right, right.
- But, it's a dark place
for these characters,
and I never judge them.
I never looked at them
as any kind of a villain.
- You can't, can you?
- Yeah, at all.
So, that was a really big important part
of doing the work.
Is not judging those characters.
Especially these ones.
And, you'll find out really soon why.
- Well, we truly get
to see your versatility
in everything that you do.
It's great to have you with us, man.
- I love a Jordan Peele film.
- Winston Duke!
(applause and cheering)
- [Announcer] If you'd
like to know more about
anything you see on Live,
just log onto our website,
at kellyandryan.com.
- [Narrator] Just when you
thought you were done painting,
you discover paint-bleed under your tape.
Not with Frog Tape.
Frog Tape is the only painters tape
treated with patented
paint-block technology.
Get professional results, with Frog Tape.
No messy lines.
No paint-bleed.
For sharp lines,
every time,
Frog it.
- [Narrator] This Summer,
Kings Dominion takes amazing
to a whole new level,
with Grand Carnivale.
June 15th through July 7th.
A celebration parading through the park.
Surrounding guests with every chance
to join the fun.
Get tickets at kindsdominion.com.
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
(gentle music)
♪ Alright ♪
(crowd cheering)
♪ Here we go now ♪
♪ Give a little bit of my love to you ♪
(gentle music)
- [Narrator] At Value City Furniture,
we know great moments
deserve great furniture.
(laughter)
Hurry in now, to the 4th of July sale,
and save 10%-30% off, store-wide.
No minimum purchase required.
Or, for a limited time,
enjoy 48 months special financing.
Now, on purchases of just $999 or more.
With payments starting
as low as $21 a month.
Get the savings you want
during the 4th of July sale.
Going on now, at Value City Furniture.
- Okay, have fun at your dad's.
- Okay, love you Mom.
(door clacking)
- Bye.
- What do you think?
- I like it.
- Get up!
- Come on.
Got him!
- Yes!
(gentle music)
(thud)
You hungry?
- Yeah.
- Alright.
(gentle music)
(lasers shooting)
- Bye.
- Bye, buddy.
- How was it?
- Dad's internet is amazing.
- Well, you know, mom's
cookies are also amazing.
That's what I thought.
- [Narrator] Get up to 1 GIG speeds
on the day you move in.
COX internet, starting at $29.99 per month
for up to 10 (mumbles).
- [Narrator] Ballston Quarter.
Enjoy indoor and outdoor shopping.
Dining and entertainment.
Right off the metro.
Check out Quarter Market.
With 10 eateries from
the regions top chefs.
With more to come.
Ballston Quarter,
Arlington's top destination
for food and fun.
- I'm Kidd O'Shea.
Check out "Cooking With
Kidd", every Tuesday.
As the areas top chefs and foodies
join me in the kitchen.
See what we're cooking,
on ABC7 News, at 4:00.
- [Narrator] "Cooking
With Kidd" is brought
to you by Ballston Quarter, and Cookology.
- [Narrator] ABC7's on your
side, this capital 4th.
With live coverage of the fireworks,
the president, and the protests.
All day, On ABC7.
WJLA 24/7 News.
And, wherever you go,
streaming on the ABC7 News app.
(adventurous music)
(cheerful shouting)
(laughing)
(adventurous music)
- [Narrator] Get the best deal on
tickets at kingsdominion.com.
It's amazing in here.
- [Narrator] Closed captioning
sponsored in part by...
- [Narrator] This is you shopping...
And this, is you maximizing.
At TJ MAXX,
get more of the brand you love,
and quality you want.
And, save every time.
It's not shopping,
it's maximizing.
Max live,
at TJ Maxx.
- [Narrator] What is love?
Two hearts?
One soul?
A kiss?
A hug?
A laugh?
What is love?
Love is all you need.
Call 1-800-Sandals.
- [Narrator] Whether
it's planned taco night,
or surprise pizza,
Zantac works when you need it.
It relieves or prevents heartburn
in as little as 30 minutes,
and lasts up to 12 hours.
Zantac.
Eat your way.
Treat your way.
(applause and cheering)
- Make sure to join us tomorrow
for an all-new Fourth of July party.
With special house-band O.A.R.
- That's very exciting.
- So, we'll be here for that.
Now, singing "Backbone",
from their album "Cage to Rattle",
it is Daughtry, let's go.
(applause and cheering)
♪ Hey ♪
♪ When you're hurting deep down ♪
♪ When you're feelin' like you're never ♪
♪ Gonna dig your way out ♪
♪ Never gonna dig your way out ♪
♪ Keep pushing up the river ♪
♪ Keep mining for the silver ♪
♪ 'Til you've shot gold ♪
♪ Gotta whether the storm ♪
♪ 'Cause it can't rain forever, no ♪
♪ I'm telling you ♪
♪ We all fall on hard times, you know ♪
♪ Each day is a hight climb, you know ♪
♪ Some days your body has to carry on ♪
♪ So you gotta show a little backbone ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ You gotta show a little backbone ♪
♪ These troubles so real ♪
♪ We're all facing temptations ♪
♪ And our own fears ♪
♪ Year after year ♪
♪ But it can't rain forver, no ♪
♪ I'm telling you ♪
♪ We all fall on hard times, you know ♪
♪ Each day is a high climb, you know ♪
♪ Some days your body has to carry on ♪
♪ So you gotta show a little backbone ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ You gotta show a little backbone ♪
♪ Are you strong enough ♪
♪ To get back up ♪
♪ When the chains hold you to the ground ♪
♪ So let's break 'em down, yeah, uh ♪
♪ Let's break 'em down ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Woah, I'm telling you ♪
♪ We all fall on hard times, you know ♪
♪ Each day is a hight climb, you know ♪
♪ Some days your body has to carry on ♪
♪ So you gotta show a little ♪
(ABC chime)
- [Narrator] Across the nation,
people are joining PENFED Credit Union,
and getting more from their mortgages.
We offer low rates,
and superior service,
to give our members the power
to purchase their perfect home.
And, everyone is welcome to apply.
Visit PENFED.org.
- [Narrator] Imagine a visibly
healthier pet in 28 days.
Purina One.
Natural ingredients in
powerful combinations.
For radiant coats, sparkling eyes.
Purina One, one visibly healthy pet.
Try new digestive health,
with probiotics for dogs.
- [Narrator] Lara Logan investigates
the ongoing border crisis,
tonight at 5:00.
(gentle music)
- If you or a loved one is
involved in a car accident,
you have two choices.
Choice number one is to do nothing,
and hope that the insurance company
doesn't take advantage of you.
Choice number two is to call me,
William McCaskill.
I'll make sure that your
medical bills are paid.
I'll make sure that you're compensated
for your lost wages.
for your pain and suffering.
Call me, William
McCaskill, at 240-724-4494.
I'd like to represent you.
(gentle music)
- [Narrator] How do you
celebrate the 4th of July?
Show up with a picture.
Just upload your best shots
using our ABC7 News app.
(bouncy music)
- [Narrator] At PENFED Credit Union,
we help you get more from your mortgage.
By offering some of the lowest
rates on mortgages around.
Everyone is welcome to apply.
Visit PENFED.org.
♪ PENFED's got great rates for everyone. ♪
- [Narrator] Live 4th of July coverage.
All day, on ABC7.
(applause and cheering)
- [Announcer] Today, on Rachael Ray.