- Thing that matters is how much we loved.
May he rest in peace.
That wraps things up for us this hour,
I'm Kasie Hunt in Washington.
Please do follow me on Twitter
and catch me every
Sunday night on Kasie DC.
Ali Velshi picks things up
from New York right now,
Hi Ali.
- Kacie, thank you,
have yourself a great
rest of the afternoon
and a happy fourth of July.
President Trump has launched a new attack
on China and Europe,
accusing them of playing a big
currency manipulation game.
He tweeted this morning
that the United States
should match the effort or
continue being the dummies
who sit back and politely watch
as other countries continue
to play their games,
as they have for many years.
Such a move, by the way,
would directly contradict
U.S. policy not to
manipulate the dollar's value
to gain trade advantages.
And the Treasury Department
said earlier this year
that no country meets it's criteria
of being labeled a currency manipulator,
although it put China
and eight other countries
on a watch list.
Donald Trump has been
pushing this issue for years.
As a candidate in 2016 he
repeatedly accused China
of manipulating its currency
and vowed to fight back.
- We can't let these other countries
manipulate their currencies,
they're devaluing their currencies,
they're making it impossible
for our country's,
our companies cannot compete.
So we're gonna have our jobs
and we're gonna make our own product
and we're gonna sell that product also,
and we're not not gonna let China
and all these countries continue
to devalue their currency.
- Now the markets
definitely seem to shrug off
the President's tweet.
In the very short pre-holiday
trading day that we had today,
markets are already closed,
The Dowgate 179 points to close
at a record high of 26,966,
the S and P 500 closed at a record as well
for the third day in a row,
the Nasdaq also closing
at a new all time record,
but let's talk about this.
What is currency manipulation?
Well it's a policy in which a
government or a central bank
sells its own currency
into the world market
and buys a foreign currency,
such as U.S. dollars,
thereby reducing demand
for its own currency.
When you reduce demand for something,
you drive the value of it down.
Now when a currency drives
down the value of its currency
makes its exports cheaper
and it makes importing more expensive
and when a country boosts its exports,
that helps lower its trade deficit,
something President Trump
has said he wants to do.
But manipulating the U.S. dollar
could have a mixed effect.
Lowering the value of the U.S. dollar
would likely boost exports
and while that's good news,
manipulating the dollar could
also cause foreign investors
to move their investments elsewhere
because a lower dollar means lower returns
on your investments, in addition,
it would effect the price of
oil, gold and other commodities
which are priced in U.S. dollars.
So bottom line is,
it's a complicated and difficult business
to manipulate the value of your
currency on global markets.
I wanna have a closer look
at this with Jared Bernstein,
he was a chief economist
and economic policy advisor
to former Vice President Joe Biden,
he's now a senior fellow at the center
on budget and policy priorities,
Jared good to see you
and I guess I wanna start by saying
you're a progressive economist,
but this is not really a partisan
issue, generally speaking.
There are schools of thought
about lowering currencies
and raising them,
but it doesn't tend to be a
Republican/Democrat issue.
- No, and in fact, Presidents
of all political stripes
have long said, we
support a strong dollar,
and in that sense, Trump is unusual.
Let me tell you something
else that's unusual.
At least half of that Trump
tweet was kind of accurate.
It is true that many of
our trading partners,
China not right now by the
way, but certainly in the past,
have managed or misaligned
their currency values
precisely in the way you just described,
to make their exports to us cheaper,
and ours to them more expensive,
and the result is a
significant trade imbalance,
which you've had in this
country for many decades.
The ironic thing is that Trump's actions
have actually made this problem worse.
They've strengthened the dollar.
- First of all, is this an achievable?
When Donald Trump says
we should play that game,
can you play that game
with the U.S. dollar,
given that the entire world
collects U.S. dollars,
not just to buy goods, but to buy oil,
to buy gold, to buy, most
commodities in the world
are priced in U.S. dollars.
So can the U.S., unlike
Zimbabwe or Thailand,
or a place like that, can
it actually manipulate
its currency deliberately?
- The answer is yes, it could,
but you raise a really
important fundamental point.
The U.S. dollar is the
primary reserve currency
of the world.
That's the currency
that, as you just said,
other countries often trade in.
Also, what's the safest asset
if you want to park your
money somewhere safe?
It's here in the U.S.,
and so that means folks
need dollars to buy
our treasury securities.
By the way, when I said
Trump is partly at the core
of this problem, by running
these very very large budget
deficits, especially at a
period of lull unemployment,
not only is our country growing faster,
and that tends to make our dollar stronger
than other currencies,
but it's pulling in more
capital from across the globe,
seeking these safe assets.
But, bottom line, yes there
are things we could do,
and frankly, things we should do.
The least we should do is identify those
who manipulate their
currencies, and amazingly,
the Trump administration has essentially
refused to do.
- Let's talk about being
the primary reserve
currency of the world.
One of the reasons the U.S. is that thing
is because it's relatively stable.
If you put your money in to
U.S. dollars to buy treasuries,
or to buy property in Miami
or whatever it is you do
with your money, the value of the currency
doesn't tend to fluctuate all that much.
If we send out a signal
that we're looking to reduce
the value of the U.S.
dollar, what's the effect
on all those people,
companies, sovereign well funds
that invest in dollars because
it's a safe, steady currency?
- You know, it's really
hard to say because we just
don't do that.
I will say, though, that
the dollar fluctuates
pretty significantly.
In fact, one of the ways
you can tell when China
and other were pegging their currency,
is that they didn't fluctuate
relative to the dollar.
They kept it at a very stable
level, a straight line.
But, the U.S. dollar goes up and down,
it's up maybe seven to 10%
over the last few months,
and we don't see dramatic
changes in any of the
kind of trades you just mentioned.
So I actually think that
it would be worth our while
to at least examine ways
in which we can push back
against those who
misalign their currencies,
because it does lead to
significant trade imbalances.
I just wanna make it clear
that most of what Donald Trump
does has made the problem worse.
- Jared, good to see you as always.
Thanks for tackling a complicated
topic for our viewers.
Jared Bernstein,
- Thank you.
- is a senior fellow
at the Center on Budget
and Policy Priorities.
While the President
creates this latest issue
over currency manipulation,
the administration
is getting legal pushback
for how it's handling
the immense backlog of immigration cases
in the U.S. court system.
A federal judge reversed a directive from
Attorney General William Barr that ordered
immigration judges to hold
asylum seeking migrants without bail.
It kept migrants detained
while their cases
are processed instead releasing them
while their cases move through the courts.
Critics said this
administration's directive
would have kept up to
40,000 migrants in custody
for six months or more
without the government
having to justify the detentions.
Now as of April, there's
a backlog of nearly
900,000 cases pending,
cases overseen by 424 judges
across the country.
The U.S. District Judge
ruled that the policy
was unconstitutional and
maintained that those
entering the United States
are entitled due process
under the Fifth Amendment.
The court concluded
among those protections
is a longstanding prohibition
against indefinite
civil detention with no
opportunity to test its necessity.
The Ninth Circuit has expressed,
"grave doubts that any
statute that allows for
arbitrary prolonged detention
without any process is constitutional."
Let's remind ourselves what the problem is
that the government is solving here.
Before this change was made,
the Department of Homeland
Security says only 7.89%
of asylum seekers from the
northern triangle countries,
Guatemala, Honduras and El
Salvador, were granted asylum
in the fiscal year of 2017.
So when people tell you that
there's this crazy system
where people are applying
for asylum and getting it,
7.89% of people from
those countries get it.
Figures from the Justice
Department show 89%
of asylum seekers do in fact
show up for their court dates,
so we're talking about 11%
whose cases are decided in absentia.
Typically, those cases are
decided against those people,
so it's just important to keep
track of what this serious
problem, or so called serious problem,
is that we're solving.
I wanna get into the
significance of all this
with MSNBC's legal analyst Danny Cevallos.
Danny, this is another
reminder that the constitution
of the United States, in most
cases, makes no distinction
between citizens and noncitizens
in its prescriptions,
so, in this case, the
Fifth Amendment clause
that calls for a speedy
trial is for everybody.
- Yes, but the government
actually argued against
what you just said, by
arguing to the court
that these migrants
are excludable persons.
They don't really fit
within the group of people
protected by the constitution.
And the court said that is not
the case in this situation.
As a criminal defense attorney,
I have to tell you that when
your client is held in custody,
there's such a difference
between a client that is held in custody
and not in custody that's
out that you can contact,
you can call, you can meet with them.
Any lawyer always provides
better legal services,
and that client is better
served, when they can fight
their case on the outside,
and not the inside.
What's different here is
that these are non criminals.
These are non criminals being detained,
and I should add, a decision
that has had such a ripple effect
that you just talked about.
Statistically, this is
causing an immense backlog
in the courts, and that's
another thing I can tell,
from experience, is a very
dangerous thing for those
with constitutional
rights, which is everyone,
which is a backlog in the criminal courts.
- That would be a problem in any country,
but it's actually something
in the United States that
is in our constitution.
- Massively so.
- It's obviously open to
interpretation what a speedy
trial is, but when you have
400 some odd immigration
judges dealing with 900,000
cases, that is going to be,
at our current pace, that's decades.
- I saw it with my own
eyes, covering this issue
at the border.
Slightly different but
the Trump administration
made a summary decision
to start prosecuting
more and more of these entry cases,
and the backlog that created
was almost overwhelming.
The courts are very sensitive to backlog,
and even the federal courts,
which may have more resources,
can be crippled.
So too can this entire
immigration process by a decision
that causes a backlog by holding people
longer than necessary.
Keep in mind, the government argued that,
look there are other cases
that say you can hold
people up to six months.
What's with this seven days?
That's such a fast timeline.
But the court here said,
no, that's not the issue.
The fundamental issue
here is whether or not
these people can be held
without any bail hearing
at all whatsoever.
- All right, thank you Danny
for clearing this up for us.
Danny Cevallos is our legal analyst.
To really underscore this
administration's policy
on immigration, I turned to this quote,
a "ticking time bomb."
That's how senior managers
at several border patrol
facilities at the Rio Grande
Valley describe the situation.
The Homeland Security Department's
Office of Inspector General
detailed the dire situation
inside these detention
facilities, giving the
public its first actual look
at the situation inside, and
despite the outright denials
from the administration,
the situation is dire.
In June, the Office, be
reminded this is the Inspector
General for the Department
of Homeland Security,
this isn't reporters, this isn't
Democratic members of Congress.
The Office visited five border patrol
facilities, and two ports
of entry, observing,
"serious overcrowding
and prolonged detention."
They found the border
patrol was holding about
8,000 detainees in custody
at the time of their visit,
with 3,400 held longer than the
72 hours generally permitted
under the Customs and
Border Protection standards.
1,500 of those detained were
held for more than 10 days.
826 children were held at those facilities
for longer than 72 hours.
On top of that, the
Inspector General found,
that the conditions under
which these children
were being detained
were below Customs and
Border Patrol standards.
At three of these five
border patrol facilities
that were visited, children
had no access to showers
despite CBP requirements
that reasonable efforts
be made to provide showers to children
who've been in detention for 48 hours.
Children had limited access
to a change of clothes,
and two facilities had not
provided any of them access
to hot meals, as is also required.
For adults, the CBP requires
that reasonable efforts
be made to allow detainees
to shower within 72 hours.
According to the report, "most
single adults had not had
a shower in CBP custody
despite several being held for
as long as a month."
No shower, for a month.
Border patrol was giving
detainees wet wipes
to maintain personal hygiene.
Most single adults detainees
were wearing the clothes
they arrived in days, weeks,
and even a month prior.
Joining me now is someone
who's been inside several
detention facilities, and is very familiar
with their conditions,
MSNBC's Jacob Soboroff.
Jacob, you have been reporting
this for a long time,
as have your colleagues here at MSNBC.
Members of Congress have gone in.
The government's response
has been these are inaccurate
reports, it's not the case,
but now we've got this
Inspector General's report from the
Department of Homeland Security,
which directly contradicts
what the administration
has been saying.
- Not only does this
Inspector General report, Ali,
directly contradict what Kevin
McAleenan has been saying,
and what the administration
has been saying,
the reporting Julia Ainsley
and I did on Monday,
also directly contradicts,
not in the Rio Grande Valley
sector, but in the El Paso sector.
We're seeing this in a systemic way
across different border patrol
sectors across the southwest border,
and that phrase ticking time bomb
is one that's getting
everybody's attention.
But I want people to
realize that this system
has been a ticking time bomb for decades.
You are housing migrants
who are coming here
for humanitarian relief, in jail cells,
and that is something that
Kevin McAleenan, frankly,
has said, but it should
not come as a surprise
that anybody in this administration,
whether it's law enforcement
or in the political branch
of the administration,
that things are as bad as they are today.
This administration has made
things worse than ever before
by exacerbating crises on
the border by making people
wait in Mexico, by telling people
that they're going to be
mired at ports of entry,
by only allowing a limited
amount of people through
every single day, so you
have people that are crossing
illegally in order to
come in to this country,
and they're being detained
as if they are criminals
when all they want is
relief, like the relief
you were just talking about,
Danny Cevallos' asylum
protection, which is
an international right.
- Kevin McAleenan has
called for an investigation,
but it's not actually about this.
It's about a different
and related case in which
there was a secret Facebook
page that was discovered,
because somebody in it
leaked it to ProPublica,
indicating the culture
that at least some of these
employees at CBP have,
because there are about
10,000 people on this page.
- The culture that you are
seeing emerge there, Ali,
is one that matches
directly the conditions
that you are seeing inside
these detention facilities,
and while we can't
ascribe the dehumanization
and the language that was
used in those Facebook posts,
to all the agents in the border patrol.
In fact I've met many
excellent men and women
who work for the border patrol.
You have to be alarmed by
what you are seeing here.
The combination of people
being held in conditions
like the ones we're looking
at on the screen, right now,
and the types of conversations
you are hearing from the,
remember these are law
enforcement agents, allegedly,
that are talking this way about people
they are supposed to be in
charge of, and supervising,
is incredibly concerning.
So, the acting Secretary
of Homeland Security,
Kevin McAleenan has
launched this investigation
from the Office of
Personal Responsibility,
and they'll look into
whether or not these agents
are meeting the standards
of the Department.
I think it's pretty clear
to see, just by reading
some of what was on Facebook
and came out through ProPublica,
that they certainly were not.
- Jacob, thanks for your
continued great reporting on this.
Jacob Soboroff for us in Los Angeles.
Joining me now is the Congresswoman
who led her fellow lawmakers
during yesterday's tour of
the largest child detention
facility in Homestead Florida,
Democratic representative
Frederica Wilson of Florida.
Congresswoman, thank you for joining us.
What'd you see when you were there?
- Thank you, Ali.
Well, I've been on this
mission for two years now,
trying to locate the girls
and do oversight over
adolescent girls, so I
went to Brownsville, Texas,
visited two facilities there,
I've been to Homestead,
and then I decided to
invite my follow colleagues
to go with me to Homestead,
just to keep up with adolescent
girls who should not be in
jail, and that's specifically
what they're in.
And they're just crowded,
thousands of young people
crowded, and noisy, in this jail.
That's what I call it, this is a jail.
They are in classes, but
I believe they should be
in public schools, and the bathrooms,
the only toilets they can use are outside.
Their dormitory is about
the size of a high school
gymnasium with just bunk
beds two feet apart,
where these children have to sleep,
and when they have to go
to the bathroom at night?
They have to get up and
go outside in the dark
in the night to go to the bathroom,
which is portable toilets.
- Congresswoman, this is
a privately run facility,
in which we as tax payers
are paying them a day rate
to accommodate these students.
A rate that, in some of these cases,
has been surprisingly high,
in excess of $700 a night,
and they're sleeping in this way.
They're living in this way.
- It is unbelievable.
Some of them are sick,
influenza is all over the place.
They're suffering, crying,
they want to see their parents,
and the sad part about it,
the girls that I finally
got to see after demanding
and staying over two hours,
after everyone had left, to see the girls.
I saw this room full of 17 year olds,
and these young people are
actually waiting for the day
that they turn 18.
And when they turn 18, they're
gonna shackle their wrists,
shackle their ankles,
and take them to jail.
And that is the saddest thing.
- What does success in this
situation look like to you?
- It's dire, because what
they're trying to do,
and what they're going to
do, is expand this facility,
instead of releasing these
children out of this facility,
giving them a home to wait on their cases,
and some of them have phone numbers
tattooed to their wrists,
some of them have little notes
that they could show me of aunties
and people who are waiting for them.
They're expanding this facility
and trying to take 1000 more.
They already have in
excess of 2000 children.
It is unbelievable,
unbelievable, and there's no way
to know whether these children
are getting the appropriate hygiene.
These little girls are going
from girlhood to womanhood,
and I just didn't like what I see.
I do not like what I see.
I'm gonna go back, and I'm
gonna keep watching these girls,
because if they can do
anything else for me,
is begin to release these
girls by the hundreds,
into the community.
- Congresswoman, good to talk to you.
Thank you for joining us,
Congresswoman Frederica Wilson of Florida.
All right
- Thank you, Ali.
- Up next, there are not
vacation days in the race for
2020 Democratic candidates on the trail,
heading into the July 4th holiday.
Campaigning in key primary states.
Among them, Iowa.
We're gonna take you there,
live, after the break,
and later in the hour, Facebook's
fight against hate speech.
Critics of the company
say it isn't going well.
I'm gonna talk to someone
who's met with leaders
from the social media giant
more than a dozen times.
What he says they should be doing
about hate on the platform.
You are watching MSNBC.
- This is political insanity.
- [Narrator] When you
need a passionate start
to the morning.
- Name one of the Democratic contenders.
Name one that you are
positive can beat Trump.
- [Narrator] You need your morning joe.
Weekdays at six on MSNBC.
(Alarm Beeping)
(Tires Squealing)
(Car Engine)
- [Narrator] Life doesn't
give you many second chances.
(Tires Squealing)
But a Subaru can.
- You guys okay?
You all right?
- [Narrator] EyeSight with
Pre-Collision Braking.
Standard on the Subaru Ascent.
Presenting the three row Subaru Ascent.
Love is now bigger than ever.
- [Narrator] Hey renovators,
time to dream bigger.
♪Wayfair, you're my new secret weapon ♪
♪You got what I need for my renovation ♪
♪I love all these options ♪
♪So much to choose from ♪
♪Bathrooms and basements ♪
♪Even my kitchen is further to sweet ♪
♪And my job is come clean ♪
♪Wayfair, here I come ♪
- [Narrator] Start your
renovation at Wayfair.com
- Pain thinks it makes the rules,
but the rules just changed.
New IcyHot lidocaine dry spray.
Instant dry technology.
No mess, no residue, fast acting relief.
Rise from pain.
New IcyHot lidocaine dry spray.
- [Narrator] Guys, got hair loss?
I know what you're thinking.
Should I shave my head?
Comb it over?
Wear a hat?
Just stop.
This isn't 1970.
Keep your hair and your confidence,
because Bosley, America's
number one hair restoration
expert can give you your
real hair back permanently.
Check 'em out today 'cause it's
their summer savings event.
You'll get a free information kit,
and the best deal of the year,
when you text SECRET to 654654.
Dude, you don't have
to look like your dad,
because this isn't your
dad's hair loss treatment.
People all over the country trust Bosley
because they're ahead of the curve.
They use the latest technology
to give you your real hair back.
And the best part,
Bosley's permanent solution
is protected by the Bosley guarantee.
Let them show you, for free,
how awesome your hair could look
with an absolutely free information kit,
and the year's best deal.
Text SECRET to 654654.
Don't miss the summer savings event.
That's S-E-C-R-E-T to 654654.
- When I book at Hilton.com,
I get to select my room
from the floor plan, free WIFI,
and the price match guarantee.
- So with Hilton there is no catch?
- The only catch is I'm never leaving.
(laughing)
No, I'm serious, I live here now.
- [Narrator] Book at hilton.com
- Have you been told you
can't get high speed Internet
where you live?
Well you can.
With HughesNet Gen5.
Experience the power of next
generation satellite Internet,
wherever you live.
HughesNet Gen5 is fast.
You'll get 25 megabits per second,
plus built in WIFI, and
there's no hard data limits.
So, wherever you live, now you can do more
of everything you love online.
Connect on social media, stay informed,
watch the latest videos, and
help your kids get ahead.
No wonder HughesNet is
America's number one choice
for satellite internet.
- [Narrator] Act now to save big
with our limited time offer.
Get free standard installation
by calling right now.
- So what are you waiting for?
Get HughesNet Gen5.
- [Narrator] To order,
call 1-800-743-9610.
Be sure to ask about our
home phone service too.
Call 1-800-743-9610 today.
- [Narrator] Or go to soclean.com
- The 2020 Democratic
candidates are hitting the road
this week, taking no break
for the 4th of July holiday.
Today they're spread across
key primary states of Iowa,
Nevada, and New Hampshire.
Now we have new polling, all
showing former Vice President,
Joe Biden in the lead,
second place alternating
between Senator Kamala Harris
and Senator Bernie Sanders.
Looking at the Quinnipiac University poll,
Harris is closing the gap, up 13 points
in the last three weeks,
while front runner Biden
is down eight points.
Harris stands at 20%, Biden at 22.
That's a virtual tie when you
consider the margin of error.
Senators Elizabeth Warren
and Bernie Sanders follow.
Senator Harris and former
Vice President Biden
are among the Democratic candidates
campaigning in Iowa today,
where a new U.S.A Today
Suffolk University poll shows Biden
continues to lead, with 24%.
Harris is in second place with 16%.
Joining me now, MSNBC's
Vaughn Hillyard who's
on the trail with Harris
in West Des Moines.
Vaughn, what's it looking like out there?
- Yeah, this what the scenes
around Iowa in the summer time
begin to look like.
Right over here, you'll see
the Senator from California,
Kamala Harris behind us here in the white.
We are here in West Des Moines.
This is the West Des
Moines Democrats picnic,
and actually right
before you tossed to me,
I saw Senator Amy Klobuchar
walking behind our camera.
They're the two candidates
in this part of the
main Des Moines area here today.
They're gonna both address
several hundred of the folks
here in West Des Moines
here this afternoon.
Then she has a town
hall, here later today,
and that conversation is,
what do you take as the
candidate from that debate stage,
where Kamala Harris
really, for the first time,
drew those contrasts with
Vice President Joe Biden,
and what does that
message look like out here
on the campaign trail?
Well, you could say this is the beginning
of the second inning, and
we'll continue to pay attention
to that as we go forward, and
what her messaging is here
to this Iowa crowd.
This is just the first stop
over the course of three days.
She'll then head to New Orleans,
and then she'll head to South Carolina
on Sunday and Monday, Ali.
- Vaughn, earlier when I
talked to you and I asked you
what Kamala Harris is going
to do to fill the space
between those moments
that she tends to have,
including the one on the
debate stage the other day,
that caused this increase in her polling,
you mentioned campaigning.
Does she have some sort of a
strategy as far as you know of
to maintain this momentum,
because part of it is that
so many more eyes are on her.
- Exactly and look at this.
A lot of this in places like Iowa,
it comes down to television markets.
For example, right here
today we're in the Des Moines
television market, tomorrow,
she's gonna be over in
Council Bluff, the
Omaha television market,
on Friday, she's gonna
be up in Sioux City.
So, it's hitting those areas,
getting your message out.
Essentially bringing in local
television channels here,
engaging, we expect to
talk with her again today,
and being engaging in that
conversation through it.
She raised three and
a half million dollars
over the course of the
three days after the debate.
That is, the campaign,
looks at that as help.
She now has 65 staffers as of today,
here on the ground in Iowa,
and so while she may make her stop here
in places like this, it's the staffers.
You can see the staffers with clipboards,
essentially getting the
names, phone numbers
of people here and trying
to get them to commit
to caucus, commit to volunteer,
because Kamala Harris as one human being,
can only do so much.
She's human, and then
it's a matter of putting
that operation in which,
the Kamala Harris campaign
believes they have a
real shot to win here.
As the polling suggests,
she's got a play to make.
Barack Obama won this place back in 2008.
She believes she can make that pitch here
(crowd cheering loudly)
and last point, you just heard the name.
A lot of times at these
events, Ali, it comes
down to local politics.
The senate candidate on
the Democratic side who
will likely take on Republican
Joni Ernst, she's here
at this event.
A lot of it's local, bringing
in those folks, the state
legislatures, building those connections,
and being out there to
support them at the same time,
which Amy Klobuchar and
Senator Kamala Harris
are here doing today.
- Vaughn, good to see you as always.
Thanks, friend.
Vaughn Hillyard in Des
Moines, Iowa for us.
Former Vice President Joe
Biden also spending the day
in Iowa after his campaign
announced it raised
21.5 million dollars
in the second quarter.
Just to compare that to Pete Buttigieg,
he brought in 24.8 million dollars,
Bernie Sanders, 18 million dollars.
NBC News corespondent
Mike Memoli is on trail
with the former Vice President.
Joins me now from Cedar Rapids, Iowa.
Mike, it's a good fund raising haul,
but by all accounts, last
week as these post debate
polls have come out, has not
been great for Joe Biden.
- Yeah, you're right, Ali,
and this is something that we've seen
from the Biden campaign,
since really the start
of this campaign in April.
Anytime they've gone through
a little bit of a rough patch,
been dealing with some
sort of controversy,
they often try to pivot the storyline
back to a position of strength.
Sometimes, that's been by
returning the discussion
to a debate between Joe
Biden and President Trump.
That's of course the big
electability argument that
really is a cornerstone of Biden's support
in a lot of these polls.
Today, as everyone's
getting ready to head off
to their holiday weekend,
and they are still dealing
with the fallout of that
shaky debate performance,
we saw the Biden campaign
take the opportunity
to put out that big fundraising number.
Yes, 21.5 million dollars.
It's not as high as what we
saw from Mayor Pete Buttigieg,
but the Biden campaign pointing out
that they haven't been
in the race for the full
90 day period of that second quarter,
and so if you average it out, per day,
he did, in fact, raise more money
than any of the other contenders,
at least those from who we heard so far.
90% of that donations have
come from small donors,
from grassroots supporters
in less than $200 increments,
and we also know that
they've been doing a lot of
high dollar fundraising as well.
He has done some 27 big
dollar fundraisers so far.
What's important to know
and what Biden campaign
also wants to point out is that a dollar
for Joe Biden goes a lot
longer than it goes for,
a dollar for even a Kamala Harris,
who we talk about a lot on our air,
but maybe the average voter
doesn't have as much recognition of.
Biden is putting a lot
of that money early into
investments in the ground game.
They say they have 50
paid staff here in Iowa.
They just doubled their
senior staff in New Hampshire.
So, yes he'll spend a lot of
that on TV ads down the road,
but they're using a lot more of that money
in investment and infrastructure
than some of the other
campaigns who are gonna be
saving a lot of that for TV ads,
just so that voters get to know them.
- That's a good point, interesting.
Mike, thanks very much.
Mike Memoli in Waterloo, Iowa for us.
The German government fined
Facebook over 2 million dollars
for under reporting the
amount of illegal content
like hate speech on its platform.
German authorities say
there were more complaints
about antisemitic content
than Facebook led on in a
recent transparency report.
The fine itself is small,
given the company's size.
It draws attention,
however, to the embattled
social media giant's clashes
with other world powers.
As the growing threat
of hate speech emerges,
this is a topic of
debate within governments
across the world.
We reached out to Facebook for comment,
but we have not heard back.
Joining me now is Rashad
Robinson, the President of
Color of Change, which
is the nation's largest
online racial justice organization.
He's met with Facebook's
Chief Operating Officer,
Sheryl Sandberg over a dozen times,
to discuss the issues facing the company.
Rashad, good to see you.
Thank you for being here.
- Good to be here.
- There's a context,
particularly in Germany,
where, as a result of the Holocaust,
they are hyper sensitive
toward hate speech,
and the degree to which it can catch on.
It does seem that the
Europeans are further ahead
than Americans are on
dealing with this issue.
- Absolutely, I mean, they are.
The fine, as you said, is small,
but the symbol of the fine,
the symbol of holding an
institution like Facebook
accountable, is serious,
and unfortunately,
we have not had that level
of oversight from the FTC
here, from congress, from the authorities
that are supposed to be stepping in when
institutions' communications
platforms, others,
do not live up to our standards.
- Why do you think that is?
Is it a will thing, is
it an understanding?
- It's a couple of things.
First of all, it is
certainly a will thing.
It's a will thing when
it comes to congress.
It's become politicized on both sides,
and I don't wanna create
false equivalencies,
because the Republicans have controlled
the levers of power and
could have stepped in
after the 2016 election
and done a lot more.
The FTC lacks the type
of teeth that it needs,
and so what we've seen is them sort of win
settlements, or get fines,
and then not be able to
implement, or hold accountable,
once Facebook then goes back
and violates some of the things
that they were called out
on in the first place.
- All right, so you have had conversations
with Sheryl Sandberg.
In fact, she's had something to say about
the census coming up.
Facebook wants to play a role
in ensuring that the census
is completed properly, and
one wouldn't have thought
that's a problem, except
that in our world of
misinformation, you can
imagine people putting
false news out about the
census and that, somehow
messing up the count.
- Yes, you cannot fill out
your census on Facebook.
(laughing)
But to that point, and this
was part of a long term
work we've been doing at Color of Change.
For the last several
years, we've been pushing
the organization to get
really clear about their
civil rights work.
Back in November, we got
them to commit to publicly
releasing their civil rights audit,
and they did the first phase in December,
which was really weak.
It didn't actually list
the structural things.
This last phase, that
they released on Sunday,
showed some more progress.
Since Sheryl Sandberg
has taken over the audit,
and put it under her office,
we have seen a marked
change in their commitment to actually
trying to solve these problems.
For us, though, the metric of success
is a different type of experience.
But as part of that, we
wanted them to really dig in,
not just into how they were going to deal
with this upcoming election,
but how do they treat
the census like an election, as well.
As a big event, where all sorts of forces
are going to try to come in,
because there's a lot at
stake, and influence it,
use racial appeals, use other things
to try to suppress
turnout, to try to suppress
participation, and so part
of this is that Facebook
makes a lot of money.
It's the largest communications platform
in the world, and they
have a responsibility
to make sure that the
technology that moves us
into the future doesn't
drag us into the past.
- All right, so lets talk about this
investigation that's
been ordered by the head
of the Department of Homeland Security,
into the secret Facebook
post that had almost
10,000 people on it in
which they were saying
remarkably sexist,
misogynist, racist things
about members of congress, about migrants.
It's 10,000 people.
We do not mean that to taint the good work
of those people in
Customs and Border Patrol
who are not involved in it,
but talk to me about how
you think about this.
This is a secret group,
who we only found about it,
because somebody in it
leaked this information,
because they thought it had gone too far.
Does Facebook have a role in that?
- Yeah, Facebook does
have a role in it 'cause
Facebook, these private
groups, they mine the data,
and then they mine the
data, and then they work
to make money off of that data.
So they've created these private groups,
and then they have
community standards about
hate, about what you can
say and what you can do
on their platform.
- [Ali] And that applies even
if your group is private?
- It should, it does apply even it does,
and it needs to apply
no matter how powerful
the people who are doing it are.
The trick here is, it's
okay to have traffic rules,
but the traffic rules
only matter if they apply
to all of us, and the fact
of the matter is that these
private groups can
exist on their platform,
and then allow for the
type of sowing and creation
of hate, and then nothing happens.
Facebook has a role in this.
I also think that the
government has a role.
The fact that people felt so comfortable,
in a space,
- [Ali] Law enforcement
Law enforcement figures
that get a gun and a badge,
and are supposed to uphold
the laws of this country
felt so comfortable as
to say some of the most
hateful and derogatory
things about people in peril,
and elected officials of color, and women,
and felt like they didn't, 'cause they're
10,000 people in the group.
- Would they say it if they
didn't have a Facebook group?
In other words, did Facebook
make them say these things,
because these people had
racist, sexist, misogynist
things to say, so do we win
if we get it off of Facebook?
- No, but I think that we
have to recognize the way
that technology and new
tools allows for this thing
to be, for this information,
to move quicker.
Lighting a match is one thing.
Lighting a match next to lighter
fluid is a different thing.
And in many ways, whether
it's YouTube or Facebook
or Twitter, these platforms
can be the lighter fluid,
so that means we have
to keep an eye on it,
and we have to pay special
attention to how this
information can spread in different ways.
Yes, someone can say hateful
things out on the street,
and that's freedom of speech, and they,
not without consequences for
their job or the workplace,
whatever, but it's freedom of speech.
It's different when you go into a group.
You are a law enforcement figure.
You don't know the other
10,000 people on that group,
and you feel so comfortable
saying these things
and doing these things.
Yes there has to be accountability.
There's accountability for all of us,
in the workplace.
- [Ali] Sure, if spoke
out on a group like that,
I'd probably get fired.
- You'd probably get fired, and
so the fact of the matter is
why should we expect less from
our law enforcement figures?
Why should we let them off the
hook when it comes to this,
and especially as we see the
images, the horrific images,
that are coming from the border right now.
We wanna make sure the very
best people are engaged
in this effort, and that's
not what's happening.
And the fact of the
matter is, is once again,
the technology that has so much potential
to bring us together
should not drag us in back.
- Rashad, good to have you here.
Thank you for being with us.
- Thanks for having me.
- Rashad Robinson is the President of
Color of Change.
All right, still ahead, Democratic voters
think it's a great idea.
Medicare for all.
New polling shows there's a
lot of support for the plan
within the party.
While some of the Democratic
candidates are already
campaigning hard on the issue,
others seem to be waiting
until the general election,
before they push hard on healthcare.
We're gonna talk about this
split strategy after the break.
You are watching MSNBC.
- [Narrator] The day after
chemo might mean a trip
back to the doctor's
office just for a shot,
but why go back there
when you can stay home
with Neulasta Onpro.
Strong chemo can put you at
risk of serious infection.
In a key study, Neulasta
reduced the risk of infection
from 17% to 1%, a 94% decrease.
Neulasta Onpro is designed
to deliver Neulasta
the day after chemo, and is
used by most patients today.
- [Narrator] Neulasta is
for certain cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta if
you're allergic to it,
or Neupogen, Fligrastim.
An incomplete dose could
increase infection risk.
Ruptured spleen, sometimes
fatal, as well as serious
lung problems, allergic
reaction, kidney injuries,
and capillary leaks
syndrome have occurred.
Report abdominal or shoulder tip pain,
trouble breathing, or allergic reactions,
to your doctor right away.
In patients with sickle cell disorders,
serious, sometimes fatal crises can occur.
The most common side effect is bone
and muscle ache.
- [Narrator] If you'd rather be home,
ask your doctor about Neulasta Onpro.
Pay no more than five dollars
per dose with copay card.
- The rights.
♪ I want it all ♪
- Spicy tuna roll!
- Sushi!
- Sashimi cone!
♪ I want it all ♪
- [Narrator] With the
Grubhub delivery app,
if you want it all, you can get it all.
Grubhub, restaurants you love, delivered.
- I had a few good tricks
to help hide my bladder leak
pad, like the old tunic tuck.
But Always Discreet is less bulky,
and it really protects,
'cause it turns liquid to gel.
So, I have nothing to hide.
- [Narrator] Always discreet.
- [Narrator] Important
message for women and men
ages 50 to 85.
Right now in areas like yours,
people have already called
about life insurance
through the Colonial Penn program,
and received their free
beneficiary planner.
Have you received your free planner?
If not, I encourage you
to pick up the phone,
and take advantage of this free offer.
In addition to your free
beneficiary planner,
you will also receive free
information on affordable
whole life insurance that
has a lifetime rate lock,
that guarantees your rate can
never increase for any reason.
If you did not receive your
free beneficiary planner,
call this number now.
Please stand by to learn more.
- I'm Alex Trebek, here to
tell you about a popular
life insurance plan with
a rate lock that locks
in your rate for life,
so it can never increase.
Did you get your free information kit?
If not, please call this number now.
This affordable plan
through the Colonial Penn
program has coverage options
for just $9.95 a month.
Your rate is locked in,
and can never go up.
And your acceptance is guaranteed
with no health questions.
See how much coverage you can
get for just $9.95 a month.
Call now for your free information kit.
- [Narrator] Call 1-800-505-6035 for your
free information and your
free beneficiary planner.
There's no obligation.
That number again is 1-800-505-6035.
Call now.
♪ Na na na na ♪
♪ Na na na na. ♪
♪ Hey hey goodbye ♪
- [Narrator] The world's
first six function
multipro tailgate,
available only on the next
generation GMC Sierra.
Get 20% below MSRP on the next generation
2019 GMC double cab
and SLE crew cab models
with a standard tailgate.
- The 20 Democratic
presidential candidates
who were on the debate
stage in Miami last week
touched on a number of major issues,
among them the economy,
immigration, healthcare,
and climate change.
Do they matter to the
voters who are gonna decide
who's gonna get a chance
to take on President Trump next year?
A new Washington Post ABC
news poll of Democratic
leaning voters, finds
that 89% of those surveyed
said healthcare is their
top issue in the 2020
election, just as it was
in the 2018 election.
Gun violence was next,
followed by women's issues.
If there's anybody in
the audience who can read
what those things say at
the bottom, please let me,
'cause I can't tell.
There we go!
All right, immigration.
There we go.
Women's issues, immigration,
then 80% at global warming,
then the economy, foreign
policy, abortion, and taxes
was of the least concern to
Democratic leaning voters.
Joining me now to take
a closer look at this
is Dan Balz, Washington
Post Chief Correspondent.
Dan, good to see you.
Thank you for joining us.
- My pleasure, Ali.
- Dan, the issue here is
healthcare, and how big a deal
it is to Democratic leaning voters,
and how many of them actually
support a Medicare for all
proposal or some sort of it proposal.
Morning Consult poll for
support of Medicare for all
shows that of all voters, a small majority
support a Medicare for all system, 53%.
77% of Democrats do.
Half of Independents do.
And only 27% of Republicans do.
So, it does seem that
support for Medicare for all,
or something like it,
is a winning strategy
for Democratic candidates.
- Well, I think there's three questions.
One is where do people
stand on Medicare for all,
or a government run single payer system,
versus the current system.
That's the first question
that people are asked.
The second is if you are in
favor of Medicare for all
or a government run system,
would you be in favor of that
if you knew that private
insurance was gonna go away?
What we found in our poll is
that there is overwhelming
support within the Democratic party among
self identified Democrats
and Democratic leaning
independents for Medicare
for all kind of program,
and that 2/3 of Democrats
say they would be in support
of that even if it meant the
end of private insurance.
Among the hardcore of the
Democratic party at this point,
or among a broad scale
of the Democratic party,
there's quite a lot of support for it.
We know that among the candidates,
there are divisions on that.
Vice President, former
Vice President Biden
is in one place.
He is resistant to go that far.
Senator Sanders, Senator
Warren, and others,
Senator Harris have come
down strongly in favor
of Medicare for all,
even if that does mean
the end of private
insurance, although Harris
has kind of equivocated
on whether she's really
in favor of that or would
be in favor of maintaining
some private insurance.
That's gonna be the debate
that we're gonna see play out.
I think that the question
for those who are opposed
to Medicare for all, and an
end to private insurance,
how strongly do they make that case?
One of the things we
saw in the debate, Ali,
was that Senator Bennet from Colorado,
who opposes Medicare for all,
made the argument that he is in favor of
reaching universal care,
but he thinks there's
a more effective way to do it.
That's the debate we're gonna see.
- And Dan, most developed
countries have some form
of universal care, universal
insurance coverage,
and there are many ways to get at this.
My sense is that by coming
up for Medicare for all,
which I happen to like as
a Canadian, 'cause it's
very similar to a single
payer system in Canada,
but it does sort of confuse the issue,
because there are people
who say they're in favor
of Medicare for all, and then as you said,
when you add in, as your
poll did, add in the question
of whether is that okay if
you eliminate your private
insurance, I think it's a
lack of understanding that
people have about the
various competing systems
that are not the one we have now.
- Well, there's always
going to be misunderstanding
when you are talking about
totally revamping the healthcare system.
We saw that in the debate
over the affordable care act
during the Obama administration.
We saw that during the
debate over universal
healthcare during the
Clinton administration.
Every time the federal
government and congress
have begun to tinker,
or radically change the
healthcare system, there is
a lot of misunderstanding.
There are a lot of concerns
on the part of people
who already have insurance.
One of the realities is, as you know,
under our Medicare system,
there is private insurance.
Most, if not all, Medicare
recipients have or need
some kind of additional
insurance to pay for the costs
that are not covered by Medicare.
There are all these aspects of it,
so part of it is a broad debate.
What's the best way?
I think one of the things I
think the candidates have heard
on the campaign trail is,
beyond the question of what kind
of system to do we have, the
question is what does it cost?
How much does it cost,
and peoples' concern about rising cost.
That's another issue that
has to be dealt with.
- So again, it's a little bit like
the climate change debate.
There's a question about what things cost,
but there isn't a really good
actuarial or mathematical
calculation of the cost of inaction,
or the cost of the current system.
Would it be easier for people to digest
if this were well priced
out, the proposals
were well priced out, and compared to,
and this is what happens if you don't.
- Well, that would be
great, but as we've seen
in past debates, getting
those cost estimates,
or getting people to agree
on those cost estimates,
is a very very difficult proposition.
You get them coming from
people with different
ideological viewpoints and
different political viewpoints,
and different political interests.
So, the debate over
what the actual cost is,
is as difficult sometimes
as what is the structure
of a new system versus the current system.
- Dan, great to talk to you, as always.
Thank you for your
thorough coverage of this.
Dan Balz, Washington
Post Chief Correspondent.
- Thank you.
- Coming up, honoring Luis
Alvarez, laid to rest today.
He is a September 11th
first responder who fought
for congress to extend health
benefits for his fellow
9/11 first responders.
After the break, I am
joined by Congresswoman
Carolyn Maloney, who has
pledged to continue the fight.
You are watching MSNBC.
- [Narrator] When you shop
for your home at Wayfair,
you get more than free shipping.
You get everything you need
for your home at a great price,
the way it works best for you.
- I'll take that!
- Honey, no.
- [Narrator] When you want it.
You get a delivery experience
you can always count on.
You get your perfect
find at a price to match
on your own schedule.
You get fast and free
shipping on the things that
make your home feel like you.
That's what you get
when you've got Wayfair.
So shop now.
- [Narrator] If you have
moderate to severe psoriasis
or psoriatic arthritis, little
things can be a big deal.
That's why there's Otezla.
Otezla is not an injection nor a cream.
It's a pill that treats differently.
For psoriasis, 75% clearer
skin is achievable,
with reduced redness, thickness,
and scaliness of plaques.
For psoriatic arthritis, Otezla is proven
to reduce joint swelling,
tenderness, and pain,
and the Otezla prescribing information
has no requirement for
routine lab monitoring.
Don't use if you're allergic to Otezla.
It may cause severe diarrhea,
nausea, or vomiting.
Otezla is associated with an
increased risk of depression.
Tell your doctor if you have a history
of depression or suicidal thoughts,
or if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
have reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor your weight,
and may stop treatment.
Upper respiratory tract infection
and headache may occur.
Tell your doctor about your medicines
and if you're pregnant or planning to be.
Ready to treat differently with a pill?
Otezla, show more of you.
- I switched to Miralax
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives forcefully stimulate
the nerves in your colon.
Miralax works with the water in your body
to unblock your system naturally,
and it doesn't cause
bloating, cramping, gas,
or a sudden urgency.
Miralax, look for the pink cap.
- Cake in the conference room.
- [Narrator] Showin' 'em you're
ready to be your own boss.
That's the beauty of your smile.
Bring out the best in
it with Crest 3D White.
Crest removes 95% of surface
stains in just three days.
Crest, healthy, beautiful smiles for life.
- My mom hired Bathfitter
to make me a new bath.
My friend Jimmy said that
when he got a new bath,
it took forever!
Jimmy didn't have to
take a bath for a month!
I didn't even get to miss one bath.
It's just not fair.
- [Narrator] Bathfitter
will remodel your bath
in as little as one day.
We've got over two million
satisfied customers,
and 35 years' experience.
Call now or visit
bathfitter.com for a free
in-home consultation.
- Hi.
- [Interviewer] Look
at how great you look.
- Thank you.
- I feel like I've been
on a diet my entire life.
- I even cut out bread and pasta.
For a day.
- And then I tried Noom.
- I feel like anyone could use Noom.
- It's an easy to stick to program
that actually changed my habits.
It changed the way I look at food.
- They say it's based on the
cognitive behavioral approach?
I just say it works.
- It just clicked.
It worked.
It worked with Noom.
- [Narrator] Visit noom.com,
and lose the weight for good.
- Last time I bought a used car,
I ended up paying too much.
It's pretty embarrassing
for me and my whole family.
The car had multiple owners and accidents.
That website didn't know.
- Carfax has a better way.
Only carfax.com can give
you the most accurate price,
based on the carfax report,
so you never have to
overpay on a used car again.
- This is anonymous, right?
- Stop the shame of overpaying
and start your used car search today,
at the all new carfax.com.
- [Holt] Good evening everyone,
breaking news tonight-
- [Narrator] Lester Holt.
- It sounds like a jet airplane out there,
but that is fire-
- [Narrator] The most trusted
TV news anchor in America.
- [Holt] That's nightly news.
I'm Lester Holt-
- [Narrator] More Americans
watch NBC News than any other
news organization in the world.
- Hundreds gathered in
New York City this morning
to mourn the loss of
a September 11th hero.
53 year old NYPD Detective,
Luis Alvarez was laid to rest
in Queens, New York this morning.
He died Saturday in hospice
care, following a three
year battle with cancer,
and more than 60 rounds of chemotherapy.
Alvarez attributed his
cancer to the three months
he spent at Ground Zero,
following September 11th attacks,
digging through the rubble.
He spent some of his final
days on Capital Hill,
pleading for extended benefits
for his fellow 9/11 first responders.
- I should not be here with
you, but you made me come.
You made me come because
I will not stand by
and watch as my friends
with cancer from 9/11,
like me, are valued less than anyone else,
because of when they get sick, they die.
- [Ali] Among the many who
attended Alvarez's funeral,
were comedian turned
activist, John Stewart,
who joined Alvarez and his
fellow first responders
on Capital Hill in the fight
for extended health benefits.
You see Stewart here,
saluting Detective Alvarez
in the final goodbye.
Next to him, you see
New York Congresswoman
Carolyn Muloney, who was at Luis Alvarez's
funeral this morning to pay her respects
to the fallen hero.
Congresswoman, thank
you for being with us.
- Well thank you for remembering,
and thank you for remembering
Detective Alvarez.
- [Ali] What was it like at the funeral?
What was the mood, given that
he was a warrior, really.
- There was a tremendous
amount of support.
The police department was there.
Hundreds and hundreds of police.
Not only from New York,
but from other areas.
His extended family.
He was at the parish
that he was raised in,
and many many friends were there.
It was a huge community gathering.
- [Ali] He was born in Cuba,
and came to American after that.
- About six years old,
but raised in Astoria,
and this was his parish.
So, he's the American dream.
He came and as an immigrant,
joined the marines,
joined the police force,
was a decorated officer,
and a detective in narcotics,
and then later in bombs.
I'd say he's a hero, a true American hero,
in working to pass the 9/11
Victims Compensation Fund.
- You remember back to those days.
What did we get wrong
about this when it came
to the first responders.
No one'll ever forget
that day, when people were
running as far as they could
to get from those buildings,
and some were lucky enough to get away,
and first responders ran the other way.
They ran into it.
- They ran into it.
- And they stayed.
- And we lost 3,000 people,
most of them responders
on that day, and we will lose
many more, thousands more,
because of those that worked at the pile.
And it's a double outrage, in a sense,
because not only are
they the victims of the
war against terror,
but our government said
come back, it's safe.
It's safe, come back and work.
Well, of course, it's not.
- The EPA had said it would be safe.
And many of these people,
we remember that plume that went on.
It was much more than month that that-
- It went on six months.
- And you could see it.
You could smell it.
- You could smell it, it was horrible.
- They worried about that,
they were going to do
their jobs and they were going
to continue to do their jobs.
They worried that they
were in danger at the time,
and they were told by the
government that it was safe.
The federal government.
So for those who say this
was a New York problem,
they were relying on
information from the federal
government to say, you're
good, keep on working.
- You've got it right,
and so not only do we have
the responsibility as
they're the veterans against
terror, but we also, they're the veterans
of misinformation from the
government that they served,
and we can never repay what they gave.
Their life, their health.
This is one way we can
make their lives better,
and those of their
families that many of them
are leaving behind, and they
aren't there to protect them.
We need to give them some support.
- [Ali] Do you believe
this is going to get done?
- I believe it's gonna
get done, and I'm hoping
we can get it on the floor
for a vote next week,
and send it over to the senate where
Mitch McConnell says he hopes to pass it,
and will pass it before the August recess.
Let's keep him at his word.
Let's get our work done in the house,
and send the bill over to him.
- Congresswoman Carolyn
Maloney, good to see you,
thank you for being with us.
- Thank you for having me.
- We'll be right back.
- I found a way to relieve my constipation
that's both gentle and fast.
New Dulcolax liquid works
naturally with the water
in my body to provide gentle relief
in as little as 30 minutes.
New stimulant free Duclolax liquid.
Puts you comfortably in control.
- [Narrator] It all comes down
to a single defining moment.
When a plan stops being a plan,
and gets set into motion.
Today's Merrill can help you get there,
with the people, tools,
and personalized advice
to help turn your ambitions into action.
What would you like the power to do?
♪ I want it all ♪
- Burgers, donuts!
Nicoise salad!
- [Narrator] Delivering from over
95,000 restaurants nationwide.
If you want it all, you can get it all.
Grubhub, restaurants you love, delivered.
- I'm Alex Trebek, here
to tell you about the
Colonial Penn program.
If you're age 50 to 85,
and looking to buy life insurance,
on a fixed budget,
remember the three P's.
- What are the three P's?
- The three P's of life insurance
on a fixed budget are
price, price, and price.
A price you can afford.
A price that can't increase.
And a price that fits your budget.
- I'm 65 and take medications.
What's my price?
- You can get coverage for $9.95 a month.
- I just turned 80.
What's my price?
- $9.95 a month for you too.
If you're age 50 to 85,
call now about the number one
most popular whole life insurance plan.
Available through the
Colonial Penn Program.
It has an affordable rate,
starting at $9.95 a month.
No medical exam, no health questions.
Your acceptance is guaranteed,
and this plan has a
guaranteed lifetime rate lock.
Your rate can never go up for any reason,
and with this plan, you
can pick your payment date,
so you can time your premium due date,
to work with your budget.
So call now for free information,
and you'll also get this
free beneficiary planner,
and it's yours just for
calling, so call now.
- [Narrator] Call 1-800-775-7230
for your free information,
and your free gift.
That number again is 1-800-775-7230.
- This is a legal alert for
users of Roundup weed killer.
In July 2018, a judge
determined that all federal
law suits could move
forward, against Monsanto,
the maker of Roundup weed killer,
over concerns that those
exposed are at risk
for developing Non-Hodgkin's Lymphoma.
And in three landmark verdicts,
the most recent in May of 2019,
for two billion dollars,
one in March 2019 for 80 million,
and another in August
2018 for 289 million,
it was concluded that
Roundup was responsible
for the plaintiffs'
Non-Hodgkin's Lymphoma.
Roundup weed killer is
the most commonly used
weed killer in American agriculture,
with an estimated 85 to 90 million pounds
used each year.
If you or someone you
love has been diagnosed
with Non-Hodgkin's Lymphoma
after being exposed
to Roundup or a Glyphosate herbicide,
you may be entitled to compensation.
How do you fight for the
compensation you deserve?
You choose the right legal team,
that has the experience and resources
to seek the most compensation
for your injuries.
Call for a free case review.
- [Narrator] Come and stop
overpaying for car insurance.
- We, in this hour, are
remembering a man who
revolutionized the American auto industry.
Lee Iacocca has died of complications
from Parkinson's disease.
Iococca became Ford's
president at 46 years old
after a series of successes,
including the creation
of the Ford Mustang.
He made his mark, though, as chairman
of rival automaker, Chrysler.
He saved the company from bankruptcy
by introducing the fuel
efficient K Car line,
which changed how the
auto industry operated,
by allowing Chrysler to make different
models of cars, using one-