- Right back at y'all.
- All right, we've got 30 seconds.
Final thoughts, Walt.
- You know, Fourth of July.
Think about it, look at the pictures.
Read the Declaration of Independence.
Remember what the Fourth of July is about
and the values that we hope to uphold.
- Kareen?
- I was thinking the same thing.
We should not be politicizing
tomorrow, Fourth of July.
It's a day of independence,
it's a day of really knowing who we are
and remembering who we are.
- We celebrate Fourth of July
in the midst of a serious moral crisis
which speaks to the
character of the country.
What will we do; who will we be?
- Meanwhile, the president
just on Twitter said
tomorrow will be, "The show
of a lifetime in Washington."
That does it for us this morning.
Have a great Fourth.
Chris Jansing picks up
our coverage right now.
- Quite a note to end on,
Willie Geist, thank you so much.
I am Chris Jansing, in
for Stephanie Ruhle,
and we begin with literal cries for help
from migrants detained
at the southern border,
fresh documentation directly contradicting
what the Trump Administration has said
that in fact show squalid
conditions at migrant centers
and that it's even more
widespread than we knew.
These disturbing and dangerous situations
detailed in a new report
from Homeland Security's
own inspector general
after surprise visits
to multiple facilities
in the Rio Grande Valley.
Those visits in June revealed
children without hot meals,
not allowed to shower,
detainees wearing the same
clothes for up to a month,
adults given only bologna
sandwiches to eat,
causing health problems.
Inspectors said that
when detainees saw them,
they banged on cell
windows and held up signs,
desperate for release.
One of those signs said,
"Help, 40 days here."
That would violate a federal court order
that migrants be held
no more than 72 hours.
A senior manager at one of the facilities
described the entire situation
as a "ticking time bomb."
Our award-winning immigration
reporter Jacob Soboroff
has seen some of these border
facilities with his own eyes,
but, wow, this report was,
even though we knew so much,
shocking to see it all there in one place.
Your reaction to this new report,
which cites immediate
health and safety concerns,
not at one or two, but
seven different sites.
- Yeah, Chris, you just read, I think,
what I believe to be the key phrase,
that this thing was a ticking time bomb.
And this is not just a
phrase that can be used
to describe the conditions
in those seven facilities
in the Rio Grande Valley.
The facility that I've been inside
is that central processing station there
in the Rio Grande Valley
where they separated more kids
than anywhere else along
the southern border.
They called it the epicenter.
A ticking time bomb
can be used to describe
the entire way that the Border Patrol
has been detaining migrants for decades.
These are prisons, jails,
and they treat migrants
as if they were prisoners,
as if they were criminals
coming into this country.
They've always been set
up as a system of intake,
jail processing-type stations,
where nobody's supposed to be there
for longer than 72 hours.
And it was only a matter of time
before they were going to see
another surge like they did
and like they are seeing along
the southern border today.
And what happens when you
have tens of thousands,
hundreds of thousands of
people coming into the country
and are being placed into tiny
little jail-like facilities
that are designed for single
adult males to be there
for an abbreviated period of time,
it's exactly what we're
seeing in this DHS OIG report
about the RGV sector,
and it's exactly what Julia
Ainsley and I reported
about what has been going on in El Paso
just a couple days ago.
- Yeah, so, a couple of weeks ago
was when this report was done,
this inspection was done.
And at the time, the DHS
said that it required
immediate attention and action,
so it sounds like, at
least in some instances,
there are no major changes
in the last couple of weeks.
Is that your read?
- The conditions are not
gonna get better quickly
in these facilities
when it comes to the facilities themselves
and the infrastructure that's down there.
I mean, that's the conversation
that's going on right now,
particularly amongst the Democrats:
What do you do about the
ways that this country
is holding migrants when
they come into this country?
But I will say, if there is
any bright spot in all of this,
just a couple months ago,
there were over 2,300,
Julia Ainsley reported this yesterday,
2,300 migrant children in the custody
of Customs and Border Protection
in facilities just like this.
As of yesterday, there were
only a couple of hundred
and they've been moved to facilities
that are operated by HHS in other areas,
not just of the southwest
border but across the country.
It doesn't mean that the
facilities are getting any better.
It means that the children, for now,
have been moved out, in large part,
at least according to what
Julia has learned from CBP.
- Yeah, I saw one report
that a baby was being held
in one of the places that was really cold
and actually their hands
and feet had turned blue,
so obviously there are
some serious problems here.
Jacob, you're gonna stay with me.
I wanna also bring in
Washington Post White House
bureau chief Phil Rucker,
Rick Tyler, a Republican strategist
and co-founder of Foundry Strategies,
Doug Thornell is a former DNC
senior advisor and principal
at the political consulting
firm SKDKnickerbocker.
So, Phil, we've now seen multiple reports
from Trump's own administration
citing these terrible conditions.
Is it changing the conversation
in the West Wing at all?
- Not much, Chris.
What we've not seen
from the administration
and from the president himself
is real moral leadership on this
or a focus on the humanitarian crisis.
Rather, there's a focus on the numbers,
how many people are crossing the border,
how many people are being detained.
We're hearing from officials
in the administration
that those numbers have been
declining in recent weeks
from a high in May.
But we've not seen the president
really forcefully take
control of this issue
and talk about the humanitarian crisis
that we see playing out
that's so well-documented
in that IG report
and in the reporting
from people like Jacob.
- And it's a humanitarian crisis, Rick,
that is unfolding in the
middle of an election season.
But even DHS responded to this new report
by saying Congress's failure to act
is incentivizing illegal migration.
But do you believe anything will change
between now and the election
or has this issue just
become too politicized?
- Well, Chris, I'd like to step
back and put it in context.
This is a massive political failure
that has occurred over decades of time,
and both parties are to blame.
And I realize a Republican
administration is in charge now,
but, look, I agree with Chairman Nadler
that someone needs to be held accountable,
but I wanna be very careful.
Yes, we need to weed out the bad apples,
but I wanna be very careful
about demonizing the Border Patrol,
'cause the problem is these facilities
that the Border Patrol is working with
are not designed to hold
families and a number of people
and especially children for
the time they're doing it.
And so, I have to say the bottom line is
if we are ill-equipped to
treat immigrants humanely,
then I would be for letting--
- Well, it's not 'if', is it?
It's not if.
You can look at these pictures, Rick,
and say they're not
being treated humanely.
They're being told to drink outta toilets.
Kids are freezing.
- Here's what I would say.
And if I were a member of
Congress, I would be saying,
"We need to release the
majority of these people today."
Maybe people who are known to be dangerous
would stay in detention,
but the majority of these
people need to be released today
because we cannot tolerate a country
that we are treating people so inhumanely.
- Well, I mean, we have 11,
11, Doug, of the candidates for president
are members of Congress,
but that ignores the fact
that ultimately the buck
stops with the president,
and it is the president
who put policies in place
that led us to where we are right now.
- Yeah, this report is
alarming, it's shocking.
A lotta the images we've seen
are alarming and shocking.
And I think it just highlights
how big of a failure
this White House's immigration policy is.
From top to bottom,
it's not keeping us
safer and it's inhumane.
And I think what we're
gonna see from Democrats
over the next few weeks,
I think there's gonna
be a hearing next week
in the Oversight Committee
where the CPB head will come and testify.
Democrats have also requested hundreds
if not thousands and
thousands of documents
from this administration on
their immigration policies,
and they've been met with no,
and the administration
has refused to turn over
a lotta this paperwork.
So, when the administration
blames Congress,
they're not cooperating with Congress
so that Congress can help solve this issue
with this administration.
So, the buck definitely stops with Trump,
and they're definitely
doing everything they can
to stonewall here.
- Yeah, in the meantime,
we just got, on Twitter,
from the acting DHS secretary, Jacob,
he just posted that he's
launching an investigation
into those Facebook postings
of the group of former
and current border agents.
What do you know about that?
- Well, what's gonna happen here
is another Office of Inspector
General investigation,
the same types of investigations
that have revealed the horrid conditions
in these Border Patrol stations.
And to hear that from Kevin McAleenan
is certainly reassuring.
But don't forget: Kevin
McAleenan also called conditions
inside these facilities unsubstantiated
as recently as last Friday.
So, I think it's important
that the department's
gonna look into this.
When you hear a culture of
9,500 Border Patrol agents
in a secret Facebook group,
this was some extraordinary
reporting from ProPublica,
talking in the way that they were,
it's hard not to give
credence to the allegations
that we hear coming out
of these facilities.
We've heard the reports from
the Democratic lawmakers
who were down there earlier this week.
I've seen certain conditions
down there with my own eyes.
And again, it's a
positive step, I suppose,
but it's certainly not gonna
alleviate what is happening,
as Rick said, right now down there.
- Yeah, and we just got a report,
I guess in the last 24 hours or so, Jacob,
that a young girl, I guess,
or a two-year-old apparently
drowned in the Rio Grande
after we saw that heartbreaking picture
of a father and his child.
- Yeah.
Again, this is another horrific story
of a family who just wanted
to escape their lives
where they were to come for a better life.
This reportedly was a Haitian national
with a child who was a Brazilian national
crossing the Rio Grande.
They were separated in the river
and a search is ongoing right
now by the Border Patrol.
If it turns out that this
child did not survive,
I want everybody to remember
that 7,000 people have died
trying to come into
this country since 1998.
The failures of our
border policy as Americans
have been systemic literally for decades
in Democratic and
Republican administrations.
No one has treated
migrants more inhumanely,
and take it from me who's seen it myself,
than the Trump Administration,
but this is a problem
that has been festering
literally for decades.
And now, finally, as far as I'm concerned,
it's refreshing, it's reassuring
to hear all of us debating how we fix it
so that this does not continue to happen.
- Yeah, well, depends on who the 'we' is,
because the president's
actually doubling down.
So you have--
- There's no doubt about that, Chris.
- Children who are dying, right,
you have these pictures
of people being held in,
reports that there are adults
who are literally in cells
that are so tightly packed
that they can't sit down,
they are standing-room-only
for a week at a time.
And yet, he's signaling more
detentions after tomorrow,
imposing fines on undocumented migrants
who don't show up for court.
Phil, I was thinking back to
when the First Lady went down
at the time of the family separation
and some people thought,
"Well, maybe the First Lady and
Ivanka will impress upon him
"the inhumanity of what's
happening down there."
But is there any scenario that you see,
having covered this president,
that suggests to you
that he will shy away from
this as a campaign issue?
- Not at all, Chris.
I mean, this is an issue
that the president believes
is a winning issue for him politically.
He believes that his tough
stance on illegal immigration
is what got him the
presidency in the first place,
it's what helped him defeat
all those other Republican challengers
in the 2016 primaries,
and he believes it's what's
gonna win him reelection.
It's why you hear him talk
about it at every single rally.
And his advisors say
that they hope this issue
stays in the headlines for every day
between now until Election Day.
And so, the First Lady
can try to put a spotlight
on the humanitarian issue,
although we've not seen
or heard anything from her
in the last few weeks here,
and Ivanka Trump can talk about
what she wants to talk about,
but the president believes
that this is how he wins reelection.
- Jacob Soboroff, thank you so much
for your continuing reporting.
Everyone else, you're coming
back, so I'll see you soon.
- Thanks, Chris.
- And coming up,
it's an all-out Iowa blitz.
Seven presidential contenders
campaigning hard just today
across the crucial first contest state.
Our road warriors are there
with new details on
Bernie Sanders' strategy,
brand new fundraising numbers,
and some revealing new poll numbers.
Plus, brand new backlash
as the tanks roll into DC
for President Trump's colossal
Fourth of July celebration,
as we get our first look at how much
the extravaganza is going
to cost you, taxpayers.
(upbeat news music)
(funky bass music)
- [Announcer] As your life
grows, so do your needs.
And with Bank of America and Merrill,
the benefits you get can grow too.
As a Preferred Rewards member,
you can enjoy priority service
and exclusive discounts
so your growing life can
be more rewarding too.
What would you like the power to do?
- [Announcer] Make fitness
routine with Pure Protein.
- [Woman] High protein,
low sugar, tastes great.
- [Man] High protein, low sugar, so good.
- [Woman] High protein, low
sugar, mmm, birthday cake.
- [Man] Pure Protein,
the best combination for
every fitness routine.
(upbeat piano music)
- [Man] Let's get down to business.
The business of family time.
And downtime.
And you time.
And forgetting what time it is altogether.
Modernized Comfort Inns and
Suites have been refreshed,
because when your business is making time,
our business is you.
Get the lowest price
guaranteed on all Choice Hotels
when you book direct at ChoiceHotels.com.
- We use Angie's list
because we can always find
great local pros--
- For any type of home project.
- I use Angie's List because it's free.
- I'm free to read reviews--
- Check their ratings--
- They can even match my
project to qualified pros.
- [Woman] Go to angieslist.com today.
- [Man] Brushing only
reaches 25% of your mouth.
Listerine cleans virtually 100%,
helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%.
Always go for 100%.
Bring out the bold.
(gasping)
- Budget meeting!
- Sweet.
- If you compare last
quarter to this quarter--
- [All] Mmm.
- [Man] It's no wonder
everything seems a little better
with the creamy taste of Philly,
made with fresh milk and r--
- You're turning onto the street
when you barely clip a passing car.
Minor accident; no big deal, right?
Wrong.
Your insurance company
is gonna raise your rate
after the other car got a scratch so small
you could've fixed it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that pen
and use it to sign up with a
different insurance company.
- [Announcer] For drivers
with accident forgiveness,
Liberty Mutual won't raise their rates
because of their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty-Liberty ♪
♪ Liberty, Liberty ♪
- [Announcer] Inflammation may cause
everyday joint discomfort.
Turmeric supports healthy
inflammation response
due to physical overexertion.
Qunol provides superior absorption
compared to regular turmeric.
Qunol, the better turmeric.
(light upbeat percussion music)
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-SANDALS.
- [Woman] For a free case review.
- Isn't this a situation of
hate the game, not the player?
This is a power play.
- This is a strategic
move from her, right?
- Why is this potentially such a big deal?
- We have more breaking news.
Why wouldn't we?
It's Tuesday in Washington.
- The wall is the sticking
point, not border security.
- Although, the promise was
a wall paid for by Mexico.
- I cannot wait to keep
talking about 2020.
I gotta tell you, I
think it's fascinating.
- Your entire business
is profiting off of other
people's information,
then you job is to keep
that information safe.
(reverent news music)
- We are now exactly seven
months away from the Iowa Caucus,
as Democratic candidates are well aware.
Seven of the contenders are
barnstorming the state today,
while the latest Iowa poll is released,
mimicking what we've
seen in national polls
since the debates.
Kamala Harris is surging in Iowa,
jumping into second and closing
in on frontrunner Joe Biden.
Elizabeth Warren also
got a post-debate bump,
while Bernie Sanders
dropped to single digits.
Our road warriors are
out across the state:
Shaquille Brewster in Iowa City,
Vaughn Hilliard in Des Moines,
Garrett Haake in Sioux City.
So, Shaq, on one hand,
Bernie Sanders had a
strong fundraising quarter.
I read that more than 800 people
turned out for his rally
yesterday in Iowa City,
yet he is dropping, not
just in Iowa but nationally.
Is there any indication his
campaign is switching strategy?
- Well, his team is saying
that they are focusing on the strategy
of slowing building this
campaign from the ground up.
And, of course, his team
is pointing to an ABC poll
that came out this morning
that shows his support
actually increasing,
ticking up just a few points.
His campaign manager had a
video briefing with supporters
or for supporters last night,
and in that briefing, he said
there'll be peaks and valleys,
but that they're going to stay the course.
But if you look at this trip to Iowa
that Senator Sanders is doing,
you notice a couple of subtle
shifts in his strategy.
Number one, his focus on retail politics.
So, there's not gonna be as many rallies
or traditional rallies that he has.
He's having ice cream socials,
though, as you probably saw last night,
he still gives long speeches
at those ice cream socials,
but he's also gonna be marching
in Fourth of July parades,
trying to meet with Iowans
and shake their hands
and enjoy this holiday with them.
But number two, he's
also gonna be focusing
on his ground game.
The campaign is opening three new offices
in the state of Iowa.
They're also going to be
highlighting their volunteer force.
They're trying to show
that they have this grassroots support
that can deliver him to
victory come February 3rd
and come that caucus time.
So, they're focusing not
only on those rallies,
but also activating their supporters
and getting them out there,
as many candidates are here
and focused on getting those Iowa voters.
- Vaughn, the debate has
catapulted Kamala Harris,
who you're with, into serious
contention, but we also know,
history tells us that debate
bounces can be short-lived.
Have you seen any
adjustments to her campaign
to capitalize on this?
And then, I also wanna
know about her fundraising,
'cause we know she made
$2 million in 24 hours,
but we haven't seen her quarterly numbers.
- Yeah, we haven't seen
the quarterly numbers yet.
The campaign tells us that
they expect to release those
in the next couple days.
But in those first three days
after her debate performance,
the campaign raised more than $3 million
in just online donations.
She had multiple fundraising
events over in California
where she raised an additional $600,000,
the campaign tells us.
And you asked the question,
"What is the position of
this campaign right now
"coming outta the debate."
And, well, the reality here in Iowa
is they now have 65 staffers,
paid staffers here on the ground in Iowa.
They looked at that
debate as an opportunity,
as being more than a debate bump,
but as an introduction of
Kamala Harris to the country.
They believe that this
summer was that moment
when people would start paying attention.
We are now, as of today,
seven months away from that Iowa Caucus.
And I asked Kamala Harris,
I was with her over in
California over the weekend,
I asked her on Sunday how she looked at
approaching this campaign going forward
and whether she was going
to take a measured approach
in continuing, as she would suggest,
prosecuting the case against
her Democratic opponents.
And she wavered in her answer
there, not answering directly.
And I followed up saying,
"Will you continue
"to draw contrasts from
your Democratic opponents?"
And she was not eager to
respond to that question.
But when it comes to the
operation they have on the ground,
they're in place and she's gonna be here
over the next three days.
- All right, Garrett,
a number of other
candidates are there today.
Money and polls, two big things.
And I do always find it interesting
when the deadline comes
that some candidates,
usually the ones who have a great quarter,
get out there ahead of everything
and then the rest lag behind.
Any suggestion on when we'll see
some of these other numbers,
and what are they waiting for?
Beto O'Rourke seemed to suggest
yesterday he had no idea
how much money he had
raised in this last quarter.
- Yeah, I don't buy that
for one second, Chris.
I'm sure that he may not
know the exact total,
but these campaigns watch
their fundraising numbers
probably closer than they
watch their polling numbers.
The candidate would know
whether or not they're on track
to hit their quarterly goals
or not at the very least.
A lotta this is news cycle management.
You'll remember even, with
O'Rourke as an example,
in the first quarter, his campaign waited
and held their numbers over a weekend.
I don't remember the news event,
I think it was a terrorist
attack that had happened
on a Thursday or a Friday
or something of that nature.
They decided not to release 'em
'cause they didn't want it
to get caught up in the wash
or look like they were bragging.
So, let's look at the calendar
for the next few days.
If you're somebody who might wanna brag
about your fundraising numbers,
today's probably your last
chance to do it for a while.
So, perhaps somebody like a Joe Biden
could be potentially
releasing their numbers early,
but you get caught up
in this holiday weekend.
And for somebody who'd
like to bury those numbers
if they were disappointing,
not what you wanted 'em to be,
Fourth of July, 5 p.m.,
great time to release
your fundraising numbers.
Now, as to Iowa itself,
we do have a ton of candidates here today.
O'Rourke is here, Biden is
here, Klobuchar is here.
I'll be covering a Mayor
Pete Buttigieg event
later on tonight.
The bottom line with Iowa is
it is still the place to go
where you can move your poll
numbers with retail events,
where being on the ground
is thought of to be the best
way to make a difference.
And part of this is 'cause of these folks
that I've been calling super-voters,
the folks who come to every event.
And you see them in all the early states,
but particularly in Iowa,
you meet these folks who take
their roles so seriously.
Listen.
Simply naming them all can be a feat.
- Pete Buttigieg, Elizabeth
Warren, Amy Klobuchar.
- Kamala Harris was there, Bernie Sanders,
Julian Castro, and Jay Inslee.
- Tim Ryan, John Delaney.
- Eric Swalwell, the
Williamson lady, O'Rourke.
- The list goes on.
But for the super-voters
of the early states,
meeting and questioning
the Democratic candidates
is a duty and a privilege.
How many of the Democratic candidates
have you gone to see so far?
- I think Biden will be 12.
- 12?!
- Yes.
- Voters in Iowa see the
most of the candidates,
with more than 150 total
events held in the state
in the month of May alone.
That gave Carol McGuire time
to meet nine candidates.
- I would love to see all 25.
I'll travel wherever we have to go.
- [Garrett] Some
super-voters have a cause.
- When I started in 2016, I was so angry.
- [Garrett] Brenda Bouchard
lost her husband to Alzheimer's.
She's asked 30 candidates
about their plans
to fight the disease over
the last two campaigns.
- Ultimately, my ideal outcome
would be that a candidate
would put out a policy around Alzheimer's.
- [Garrett] Some super-voters
are semi-professionals.
Anthony Geron in Nevada is an activist
with a group called Make the Road.
- I wanna be as educated as possible.
I don't wanna be caught off-guard.
- The ACLU trained Kevin Leuters,
who comes to events with
a list of questions.
What's your method to getting a candidate
to answer your question?
- Well, to corner them.
Usually, if there's a Q&A session,
my arm goes up quicker
than anybody else's.
- (laughing) The fastest draw in the West?
- The fastest draw in the West.
I've been trained well.
- [Garrett] Marc Korver has no trouble
catching a candidate's eye
for a chance to get a signed baseball
and to get close to history in the making.
- To me, that's more important,
you personalize yourself,
'cause sometimes people think presidents
being larger than life.
This makes them, I say it
brings out a more human side.
- [Garrett] For all of these super-voters,
picking presidents is
a participatory sport.
Watching a debate isn't
enough; they want to shape it.
- I'm one of many voices.
But if I have a voice
here in New Hampshire,
I'm going to use it to
the best of my ability
to try to make a change.
- Chris, technology has
changed the game here too.
The ease of shooting a video
of your interaction with a candidate,
posting it on social media,
has given these
super-voters even more power
to shape the narrative, shape
the discussion in these races.
- Garrett Haake, who's
braving the rain for us
this morning in Sioux City,
Vaughn in the sunshine,
and Shaq's near a coffee pot,
so you tell me who's got it going on.
Thank you, gentlemen, appreciate it.
And up next,
the legal battle over
President Trump's tax returns
escalates to a whole new level,
with Democrats following through
on a potentially game-changing threat.
(upbeat news music)
- This is political insanity!
- [Announcer] When you
need a passionate start
to the morning--
- Name one of the Democratic contenders,
name one that you are
positive can beat Trump.
- [Announcer] You need your Morning Joe,
weekdays at 6:00 on MSNBC.
- I have one kid in each
branch of the military,
but I'm command central.
- [Announcer] Why Elaine chose Verizon.
- It's so important to us
that Verizon is supporting
military families.
When I have a child deployed,
having a reliable
network means everything.
So, when I get a video chat
and I get to see their face,
it's the best thing in the world.
And I've earned every
one of these gray hairs.
Military moms, we serve too.
- [Announcer] The network
more people rely on
gives you more,
like military plans with a
special price on unlimited,
$100 per line,
and big savings on our best
phones when you switch.
That's Verizon.
- [Announcer] When you shop
for your home at Wayfair,
you get more than free shipping.
You get everything you need
for your home at a great price,
(doorbell ringing)
the way it works best for you--
- I'll take that. (laughing)
- [Mom] Wait, honey, no.
- [Announcer] When you want it.
You get a delivery experience
you can always count on.
You get your perfect
find at a price to match
on your own schedule.
You get fast and free shipping
on the things that make
your home feel like you.
That's what you get when you've
got Wayfair, so shop now.
- [Announcer] Cooling down
with a refreshing drink
is always nice.
Introducing the Ice Genie,
the revolutionary
space-saving ice cube maker
that can replace
as many as seven
traditional ice cube trays.
Ice Genie is easy.
Just fill and chill.
Then lift out the inner cylinder
and empty the cubes into the bucket.
Ice Genie can hold up to
three batches of ice cubes.
That's 120 ice cubes at a time.
Wow!
Make all your cold-drink dreams come true
with the Ice Genie.
Available at these fine retailers.
- [Announcer] If you live with diabetes,
why fingerstick when you can scan?
With the FreeStyle Libre 14-day system,
just scan the sensor with your reader,
iPhone, or Android, and
manage your diabetes.
With the FreeStyle Libre 14-day system,
a continuous glucose monitor,
you can check your glucose levels anytime
without fingersticks.
Ask your doctor to write a prescription
for the FreeStyle Libre 14-day system.
You can do it without fingersticks.
Learn more at FreeStyleLibre.us.
(light upbeat music)
- Can you love wearing powerful sunscreen?
Yes.
Neutrogena Ultra Sheer.
Unbeatable protection helps
prevent early skin aging
and skin cancer with a clean feel.
The best for your skin.
Ultra Sheer.
Neutrogena.
- Discover.
- Hi!
Do you have a travel card?
Yep, our miles card.
Earn unlimited 1.5 miles
and we'll match it at the
end of your first year.
- Nice!
I'm thinking about a scuba diving trip.
- [Operator] Ooh!
- (gasping) Or not.
- You okay?
- Yeah, no, I'm good.
- [Announcer] Paid spokesperson.
- This is a legal alert for
users of Roundup weedkiller.
Roundup has been designated
as a probable human carcinogen
by the World Health Organization.
In July 2018, a judge determined
that all federal lawsuits
could move forward against Monsanto,
the maker of Roundup weedkiller,
over concerns that those exposed
are at risk for developing
non-Hodgkin's lymphoma.
Landscapers, those who work
in the landscaping industry,
farmers, and heavy
exposure residential users
where Roundup weedkiller is used
are at risk for developing
non-Hodgkin's lymphoma.
Roundup weedkiller is the
most commonly used weed killer
in American agriculture,
with an estimated 85 to 90
million pounds used each year.
If you or someone you love
has been diagnosed with
non-Hodgkin's lymphoma
after being exposed to Roundup
or a glyphosate herbicide,
you may be entitled to compensation.
How do you fight for the
compensation you deserve?
You choose the right legal team
that has the experience and resources
to seek the most compensation
for your injuries.
Call now.
- [Announcer] You save.
- Now to that big escalation
in the Congressional Democrats' fight
to see President Trump's taxes.
The House is suing the Treasury Department
and the Internal Revenue
Service over his returns
after their requests and
then subpoenas of the returns
was ignored by Treasury
Secretary Steve Mnuchin
and IRS Commissioner Charles Rettig.
So, the federal courts now get the case,
which could ultimately be
fought in the Supreme Court.
I'm joined now by Charlie
Savage, a New York Times reporter
who has been covering this for months
and is also an MSNBC contributor,
David K. Johnston, a Pulitzer
Prize-winning journalist
who has written multiple books
on the president and his administration.
He is an expert on tax issues
and has been looking into the
president's returns for years.
- So, Charlie, in the
lawsuit, the committee claims
that the White House's refusal
to comply with their subpoena
is, and I'm quoting here,
"An extraordinary attack on
the authority of Congress
"to obtain information
needed to conduct oversight
"of Treasury, the IRS, and the tax laws."
So, what are the questions
here for the judge,
who could obviously order
the defendants to comply?
- That's right.
Well, the question here
is whether the broader Trump strategy
of stonewalling Congress,
which is to say that all of its requests
for oversight information
are illegitimate,
will withstand judicial scrutiny.
The Trump Administration has
been fighting all subpoenas
and requests for information
ever since the House was taken over
by Democrats six months ago
by saying that Congress only has authority
to request information
if it's thinking about
how to write a new law
and it doesn't have authority
to request information
to uncover wrongdoing,
and that even when it says
it's trying to write a new law,
like in this case,
the Executive Branch can second-guess that
and say, "That's just a pretext;
"this is really about exposing information
"for political purposes.
"That's outside your authority
and you can't do that."
Two courts have already
rejected that argument
at the District Court level
for subpoenas by Congress
to financial firms
for Trump Organization records.
Now, a third judge will get a crack at it,
and this is the first one
coming from Congress itself.
- So, here's part of the
White House statement.
"Chairman Neal's willingness
to use his powerful committee
"to go after his political opponents
"is a danger to democracy.
"The committee has no
legitimate legislative purpose
"for which is can demand
the president's tax returns,
"and it is evident
"that they are only
interested in partisan games."
So, Charlie, is this partisan?
What could be in those returns
that would be of interest to Congress?
- Well, is it partisan?
I mean, you'd have to be utterly naive
to think this is not political.
Of course it's political.
The question is just
whether it's within
Congress's authority to do it
regardless of its motive.
On the face of it, the law
says Congress, this committee,
can request any individual's
tax returns, period.
It doesn't set a limit.
And so the executive branch
is kind of inventing one,
and we'll see whether a
judge goes along with that.
But why would they want it?
They've said in other occasions
that they want to see these returns
because every president until
now has released his returns
and they wanna enforce that tradition.
They wanna see what kind of
financial dealings Trump has
that may have run afoul
of the Constitution's bar
on receiving emoluments
from foreign governments.
They wanna see what his business
entanglements with China
and with Russia and with other governments
that he might have foreign
policy decisions about are.
And they wanna see what the
president's financial health is
and whether it lines up
with what he claims it is on the scale.
So, there's all kinds of reasons
that they want to see these
and they clearly also
wanna make them public.
- But, David, what they
wanna put out there
is that the reason
they don't think they
should turn them over
is kind of protecting the office,
not protecting something
that might be in there
that would lead to
problems for the president.
Tell us, in that context, what you know
about the president's returns
and what might be in there.
- Well, all of the arguments
that are being made
by the administration
are simply cover for
hiding Trump's tax returns.
And the argument that
the court's going to hear
is that Trump himself has made the case
that there is a legitimate
legislative purpose.
He has complained
that he's being excessively
audited by the IRS.
He claimed recently he's being audited
because he's a Christian.
He claims that he's being treated
differently than other presidents.
So, he, with his own words,
has made the case here
that Congress should be looking at this
as part of its oversight of
the Internal Revenue Service.
And in the history of this
law, which was enacted in 1924,
there has not been until now
a single case that there's any record of
of the IRS not turning over
information when requested.
In fact, the Joint Committee on Taxation
has three staff members who
work in the IRS building
because they review tax
returns every day of the week.
- So, Mick Mulvaney, Trump's
acting chief of staff,
has said that the Democrats
will never see Trump's returns.
David, it sounds like you
wouldn't place a bet on that.
- They will see Trump's tax returns.
Now, if this isn't settled
by the end of this Congress,
the clock will have to
restart with new litigation,
but we will eventually
see Trump's tax returns,
no question about it.
And in addition, the New
York State Legislature
and the governor have signed legislation
that provides to the
Ways and Means Committee
and other congressional
tax-writing committees
the New York State information
from Trump's tax returns.
People watching this shouldn't forget,
Trump won't even release the audit letter,
an absolutely anodyne document
that would say if he's under audit.
He claims he's audited ever year.
The only individuals who
get audited every year
are people the IRS has
strong reason to believe
are tax cheats,
but they haven't managed
to nail the case yet.
- So, to David's point
really quickly, Charlie,
when might we get us something on this?
When might this all be settled?
Could it indeed go past 2020?
- Oh, easily.
So, a district court
judge has to look at it.
Assuming Trump loses, he'll appeal.
An appeals court will have to look at it.
Then whoever loses that
will appeal to the full appeals court.
And then whoever loses that
will appeal to the Supreme Court.
It's very easy to see this
dragging on for a long time.
On the other hand, those two
cases I mentioned earlier
involving subpoenas to private
financial and banking firms
holding Trump Organization records,
the first-line judges who
looked at both of those cases
moved them very quickly.
In a matter of weeks they
said, "No, Trump is wrong,"
and ordered the firms to
comply, and then Trump appealed.
So, it's possible that judges
can choose to move this along
and not let it be dragged out.
But for now, it's clearly the strategy
of the Trump legal team to
just buy time and stall.
- Charlie Savage, David K. Johnston,
great to see both of you, thank you.
And up next, as tanks roll
into the nation's capital
ahead of tomorrow's festivities,
why some former military
officials are expressing concern
about President Trump's controversial
Fourth of July celebration.
(upbeat news music)
(alarm buzzing)
- [Announcer] This is your wake-up call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis
month after month, the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
Humira can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
Humira targets and blocks
a source of inflammation
that contributes to joint
pain and irreversible damage.
- [Announcer] Humira
can lower your ability
to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes fatal infections,
including tuberculosis,
and cancers, including
lymphoma, have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening heart failure.
Tell your doctor if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections are common
and if you've had TB, hepatitis B,
are prone to infections or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start Humira if
you have an infection.
- [Announcer] Help stop the clock
on further irreversible joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here, right now, Humira.
- I switched to MiraLAX
for my constipation.
- [Announcer] Stimulant laxatives
forcefully stimulate the
nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX works with the water in your body
to unblock your system naturally.
And it doesn't cause bloating,
cramping, gas, or a sudden urgency.
MiraLAX.
Look for the pink cap.
♪ Na-Na-Na-Na ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
- [Announcer] The world's
first six-function
MultiPro Tailgate.
Available only on the
next-generation GMC Sierra.
Get 20% below MSRP on
next-generation 2019 GMC Double Cab
and SLE Crew Cab models
with a standard tailgate.
(doorbell ringing)
(shrieking)
- Wait, it can't be, I'm not ready!
I do spin class!
What?
The refrigerator?
Oh, come on!
Do you know how much this cost me?
You're killin' me!
Let me rephrase that.
- [Announcer] Your
refrigerator, air condition,
water heater will all die sometime.
When they do, your homeowner's
insurance won't cover them.
Be sure your budget's protected
with an American Home
Shield home warranty.
We help cover the cost
to repair or replace
components of your systems and appliances,
no matter their age.
Limitations and exclusions apply.
Home systems and appliances
will eventually die.
Count on American Home Shield
to get you back up and running.
- [Woman] Ugh, the air condition too?
- [Announcer] Be sure
your budget's protected.
For free information, call 1-800-979-5629.
That's 1-800-979-5629.
Be sure with the Shield.
American Home Shield.
- [Announcer] Make fitness
routine with Pure Protein.
- [Woman] High protein,
low sugar, tastes great.
- [Man] High protein, low sugar, so good.
- [Woman] High protein, low
sugar, mmm, birthday cake.
- [Announcer] Pure Protein,
the best combination for
every fitness routine.
- Most homeowners draw a blank
when asked what their
home projects should cost.
That's why, at HomeAdvisor,
you can see what others paid
for similar jobs in your area.
Start your next home project
knowing what you should pay.
Go to HomeAdvisor.com or
download the free app.
- You've tried so many moisturizers,
but one blows them all outta the water.
Hydro Boost, with hyaluronic acid
to plump skin cells so it bounces back.
Neutrogena.
And try our hydrating makeup.
- So, here's the promise
that President Trump
is tweeting this morning.
He'll give the US, "The
show of a lifetime,"
at tomorrow's expanded July
4th celebrations in Washington.
Well, here's one look at
how that's coming along.
Politico's Heather Caygle
tweeted that a crane had
to be used to move a tank
after the flatbed truck transporting it
was unable to clear an overpass.
We have new images as well
of the tanks stationed around the Mall,
including the Lincoln Memorial,
where President Trump
will give his address.
There are also reports that
the cost of the extravaganza,
an event the president has
wanted for two years now,
will balloon far beyond
the usual $2 million
for a DC Fourth of July,
and the higher cost will mean
less money for national parks.
The Washington Post reports
the National Park Service has
diverted $2.5 million in fees
to cover some of the costs.
NBC's Monica Alba joins us now
from the National Mall with more.
Hey, Monica, we're just a day away.
We know that the Pentagon
has been scrambling
to get together on short notice
what the White House is asking for.
What are you seeing on the ground?
- Exactly, Chris.
As you can see right here next to me,
these are actually two
Bradley Fighting Vehicles.
This is just some of the military might
that is expected to be on full display
tomorrow night here, of course,
on the National Mall right behind me.
And this is just some of an example.
You mentioned, of course,
they were moved overnight on
trains and then flatbed trucks
because these tanks are exactly so heavy.
And of course, this is the president,
he fell in love with this
two years ago in Paris
on Bastille Day and wanted to recreate it.
But a lot of critics are questioning
whether he's gonna be able
to kind of keep this event
that is typically nonpartisan partisan,
whether he's going to go
into more of a campaign mode.
Asked to kind of preview
what speech he's gonna give
and whether it's gonna be
able to unify all Americans,
he said, "I think so,"
but in the same answer
he also talked about
the healthcare plan that the
Democrats have put forward
destroying the country,
so that's a little bit of a fine line.
Now, everything here is still open.
You can see, of course,
this other Bradley Vehicle
and the Lincoln Memorial.
So, tourists are here, it's
just another hot summer day.
Tomorrow, this will look
a little different though,
with many people expected on the Mall.
Chris?
- Monica Alba, thank you for that.
Phil Rucker is back with me,
as well as highly-decorated
retired Army Colonel Jack Jacobs,
a Medal of Honor recipient and
MSNBC military contributor.
So, Phil, your paper reports,
"This year's gathering on
the Mall marks a departure
"because presidents have not
traditionally participated
"in the nation's Independence
Day celebration."
So, why Independence Day
if you're gonna do a military parade?
What are you hearing about
how this all came about,
'cause it was all pretty fast?
- Yeah, Chris, well the president
wanted to do a military parade
and those plans actually were thwarted,
in part by the DC government
over concerns about cost
and just infrastructure problems
with rolling tanks through
the streets of a city.
And so, the parade was not to be.
The president seized
on this July 4th moment
as a chance to put his own mark
on what has historically been
a decidedly nonpartisan celebration
in the nation's capital.
He's wanted to have bigger
fireworks than normal.
He's wanted to put
himself at center stage.
He's given out VIP tickets
to his political donors.
And meanwhile, it's being
funded by the government,
not by his campaign.
And, in fact, my colleagues at the Post
have reported last night
that $2.5 million in
national park entrance fees,
these are the fees that you pay
when you go to visit
Yosemite or Yellowstone
or any of these national parks,
that that money has been
diverted away from the parks
to help fund tomorrow's celebration.
- There are, Colonel Jack, as you know,
military parades around the world,
which, again, as Phil pointed out,
was originally what the president wanted.
Russia has Victory Day,
Iran, National Army Day,
we mentioned that he was at Bastille Day,
which is kind of where he got
the idea that he wanted this.
But do you share the
concerns that we've heard
from some former military officers
who say, "Look, you've got to
keep this stuff apolitical,"
and it clearly is not?
- Yeah, I do, and people
I talk to do as well.
We've had a long history and tradition
of having an apolitical
Fourth of July celebration.
We're celebrating the
founding of the country,
not celebrating our military might.
The thing that concerns me the most
is the fact that we don't have
to show our military might.
There are tank countries and
there are non-tank countries.
We are a non-tank country.
Iran is a tank country, North
Korea is, Russia, China.
Those are all tank countries.
We don't have to demonstrate.
Matter of fact, it's part of our strength
that we don't have to demonstrate
our strength in this way.
And the conclusion that one draws
is that this is merely a,
it's not even a
thinly-veiled campaign event.
It looks exactly like a campaign event.
And it panders to the least savory
of all of our political notions, Chris.
- Well, the other thing, I think,
that we're seeing here a little bit, Phil,
is that this is, in some ways,
not unlike the president tweeting
he'd like to meet Kim Jong-un at the DMZ
and then there's this big scramble, right?
The new press secretary gets
caught in the middle of it
and all these things have to
be done at the last minute.
Sounds like that's the same thing
that happened to the
Pentagon in this case.
- Yeah, Chris, part of what's
going on here, I think,
is that the president himself
is trying to produce this event.
Remember, his background is in putting on
reality television shows.
He cares intensely
about the staging of
his political rallies,
about what goes where,
about what equipment would be involved.
And he's been very hands-on
in the last few weeks
in putting together the
plans for the Fourth of July
on the Mall.
- Wait just a second.
Colonel Jack, does it bother you,
with everything that is
going on in the world,
multiple nuclear threats among them,
that this is how the president
is spending his time?
- Well, of course it's bothersome.
Look, he's not alone.
All presidents are always
campaigning, always have been.
But this is really in-your-face
and it's clear that his focus
is less on the kinds of
things that keep us free
than things that look
like they keep us free.
The decision-making,
you just have to go back a couple of weeks
and take a look at the
paucity of intelligent
and strategic decision-making
that has taken place just
in the last few weeks,
with Iran being aggressive in the Gulf,
the attacks on the ships there,
what's taken place in Iran now,
plussing up its nuclear capability.
No response from the
United States to speak of.
Same thing in North Korea.
China is spreading out
across the South China Sea,
and so on.
There are lots and lots of things
we need to do with our
military; this isn't one of 'em.
- Colonel Jack Jacobs,
always good to see you.
Happy Fourth.
And to you, Phil Rucker, as well.
Thanks, guys.
- Thank you.
- Up next, it might not come as a surprise
that polls show Elizabeth Warren
and Kamala Harris getting a bump
after their debate
performances, but a new analysis
shows exactly where their
gains are coming from.
(upbeat news music)
(light upbeat piano music)
- [Announcer] Let's get down to business.
The business of family time.
And down time.
And you time.
And forgetting what time it is altogether.
Modernized Comfort Inns and
Suites have been refreshed,
because when your business is making time,
our business is you.
Get the lowest price
guaranteed on all Choice Hotels
when you book direct at ChoiceHotels.com.
- [Woman] Thanks, Golden Corral.
Dan gets a slow-smoked sirloin
and my little trio are as happy as shrimp.
Oops, clams.
And Mom got it all,
hook, line, and sirloin.
- [Announcer] The slow-smoked
sirloin and shrimp trio.
Golden Corral, the only one--
- [Crowd] For everyone.
- [Announcer] Driverless
cars or trips to Mars, $4.95.
Delivery drones or the
latest phones, $4.95.
No matter what you trade,
at Fidelity, it's just $4.95
per online US equity trade.
- [Announcer] Pain, swelling, stiffness.
When your hands hurt, you can't function.
Until now.
Introducing the new Copper
Fit Compression Gloves
with Sure Grip technology
to give you more power,
more control, and more agility than ever.
Our most advanced copper-infused
compression fabric
woven into an ultra
lightweight performance glove
that fits like a second skin
to support relief and
recovery of sore muscles
and painful joint stiffness.
And new Sure Grip bands built in
to provide a strong, non-slip grip
for more power and control.
- You need total control of your hands
when you're doing anything
with construction.
Your hands are your livelihood.
The Copper Fit gloves are great.
The grip is outstanding here
with these different ribs.
It makes my hand a lot more usable.
It just feels like you're
ready to start the job.
- The gloves have been
a game-changer for me.
They help with flexibility
and pain and soreness.
They allow me to do my job even better.
- [Announcer] Breathable wicking fabric
with an open-finger design
for full range of motion,
feel, and control.
- They relieve my pain.
When I grab something, I'm not in pain.
The support or whatever
magic these things do,
I don't know what it is,
it doesn't matter to me
what it is, it works.
- I get a lotta pain
and it can make it difficult
to do the smallest thing.
- While I'm wearing this,
I do not have any pain.
I can use it on the
keyboard, I can use my phone,
I drive with it, I sleep with it.
I love this glove.
- [Announcer] The new Copper
Fit Compression Gloves
with Sure Fit technology.
Relief from painful muscle
and joint soreness guaranteed
or your money back.
Call 1-800-258-3808
or on the web at
GetCopperFitGloves.com for only $19.99.
Order right now and your shipping is free.
- I tried it, I use it, I know it works.
- Copper Fit gloves definitely
just make my life better.
- I've used Copper Fit before.
This has helped my hands so much.
These things work.
- [Announcer] Feel better with
copper-infused compression.
Ask for it by name.
Copper Fit Compression Gloves.
(soft pop music)
- Can you love wearing powerful sunscreen?
Yes.
Neutrogena Ultra Sheer.
Unbeatable protection helps
prevent early skin aging
and skin cancer with a clean feel.
The best for your skin.
Ultra Sheer.
Neutrogena.
- [Man] We'd love some help with laundry.
Spray and scrub anything with a stain.
Wash the really dirty clothes separately.
- [Announcer] New Tide Pods
with upgraded four-in-one technology
unleash a foolproof clean in one step.
- Aw, you did the laundry.
- [Announcer] It's got to be Tide.
- Knowledge is power.
I want to help empower you
to decide how this country
should be governed.
- [Announcer] More
Americans watch NBC News
than any other news
organization in the world.
- This morning, a new
Washington Post/ABC poll
shows that while Kamala
Harris and Elizabeth Warren
both did get a boost from
strong debate performances,
Joe Biden still leads.
And that lead has diminished,
though he remains at the top
of every single national poll
we've seen since the debates.
And this morning, we may know why.
It goes beyond Iowa and
beyond the nomination.
45% of voters think
that he is the candidate
who can beat Trump in
the general election.
Joining me to weigh in, Liz Alarcon,
founder of Pulso, a
social media organization
dedicated to top issues
affecting Latino-Americans.
Rick Tyler and Doug
Thornell are back with me.
Doug, do you think it's that simple?
Biden is still in the lead
because he's viewed as more moderate
and Democrats think he
can win in the general?
- Well, I think it's also because
he's got a broad coalition of support.
African-Americans have
been a base of his support
since he started.
He's doing well with older voters.
He's doing well with moderate voters.
So, he's got a broader coalition.
I think, depending upon
what polls you look at,
they're saying different things,
so I would just be cautious
about interpreting them too much
until maybe a couple weeks
after the debates have passed.
But clearly--
- Well, let me show you something though,
'cause this is interesting,
because FiveThirtyEight
did something really smart.
They took a group of voters
before the debates and polled them,
and then they did one after the debate.
So, you actually see how the
debates really moved things.
Look at this.
The big winner, clearly,
Kamala Harris, up 9.4%.
Julian Castro, Elizabeth
Warren also gaining.
But look at Joe Biden, down 6.8%,
Beto O'Rourke, Pete Buttigieg
also losing ground there.
What do you make of that, Liz?
- I would say that there are several polls
that we should be looking at.
The Univision poll that came out yesterday
that surveyed Latinx voters
showed that Kamala Harris
went up from sixth place up to first
and Julian Castro also had a big jump.
He's now in second place
among those Latinx voters
that were surveyed.
And we know that the Latinx community
is going to be the largest
minority voting bloc in 2020.
- [Chris] How do we know that?
How do we know that?
- Well, many studies from Pew have shown
that our community is increasing,
not only in voting age
but in numbers overall.
So, the number of folks
in the Latinx community
that are turning 18 is, I think,
around 800,000 every single day,
and so we know that the
candidate that is elected
in 2020 in the Democratic primaries
will not win the general
election without the Latinx vote.
- So, there is a lotta talk
about who won, who lost.
And, Rick, I think, obviously,
these polls aren't just
being watched closely
by these campaigns,
they're also being watched
by the Trump campaign.
What do they take away from
what we've seen so far?
- Well, I think the
imprimatur of invincibility
on Joe Biden has been removed.
And I think Kamala Harris is right,
Kamala, I'm gonna learn
how to pronounce that name,
Harris is right where she wants to be,
because you do not wanna be
the frontrunner this early out.
Being in second place is
a terrific place to be.
- [Chris] Would Trump rather
run against her than Biden
or vice versa,
or any of the other
candidates, for that matter?
- I don't know, I think
it's too early to say.
I don't think anything's set in stone.
I think the leaders are
gonna shift a little bit
and there's gonna be a
lotta people that drop off.
But what's significant is
Joe Biden just lost ground
in every single demographic,
among all the ideological spectrum,
and Kamala Harris gained
in every single one,
particularly black voters,
which probably came out of Joe Biden.
But Elizabeth Warren was
kinda flat, actually.
She has lost significant
support among black voters.
But Joe Biden still
remains the top of the heap
and the person that people
believe will beat Donald Trump.
But Kamala Harris has
improved significantly
her believability that
she can beat Donald Trump,
and that's a huge factor
with Democratic voters this time around.
- Yeah, I mean, obviously, Doug,
you gotta build a winning coalition.
There's a new piece by NBC
News reporter Alex Seitz-Wald,
who writes, "Harris stunned Biden.
"But can she meld a
winning Obama coalition?"
How do you build that?
And who, from your
perspective at this point,
is doing the right things
to move in that direction?
- Well, you start building it
by putting organizers on the ground,
and I think Kamala Harris's campaign
is doing that more and more,
both in Iowa and South Carolina.
Elizabeth Warren has a huge field staff
that she's invested in in a
number of key early states.
And so, having that direct
person-to-person communication
is really important in terms
of building out your coalition.
Moments like the debate
are really important.
When these candidates start to advertise
and get their message out across
mass communication mediums,
that's gonna be really important.
But, look, I would take issue
with one thing that Rick said.
Look, I think that with Kamala Harris,
there is a lotta room to grow.
And a lotta people didn't
know her or Elizabeth Warren,
so they took advantage of that
and both of them did really well.
Elizabeth Warren did very
well, I think, as well.
- Seize the day, right?
Liz, Rick, Doug, thanks to all of you.
Happy Fourth.
- Thanks, Chris, Happy Fourth.
- And coming up,
Congresswoman Rashida Tlaib will be here
to talk about her visit
to one of the controversial
detention centers in Texas
and talk about what she witnessed.
(upbeat news music)
- [Announcer] Thank you to the obstacles
that stand in the way of our vacation.
Thank you to the detours and delays
and everything that gets
in the way of summer.
Because you remind us of
our love for the open road.
("Summer in the City"
by The Lovin' Spoonful)
Summer starts now.
Hurry into the BMW Summer On sales event
and get up to $4,500
credit on select models
now through July 31st.
- [Announcer] Make fitness
routine with Pure Protein.
- [Woman] High protein,
low sugar, tastes great.
- [Man] High protein, low sugar, so good.
- [Woman] High protein, low
sugar, mmm, birthday cake.
- [Announcer] Pure Protein,
the best combination for
every fitness routine.
- We use Angie's List
because we can always find
great local pros--
- For any type of home project.
- I use Angie's List if
I need to find a plumber.
- An electrician.
- A painter.
- I always use Angie's
List because it's free.
- It's free for me to read reviews
written by real customers.
- We can check their reputation
and make sure they do quality work.
- And now, to save time,
Angie's List can actually match my project
to a few qualified pros
who can do the job.
- [Announcer] To get the most
reviews from real customers
all for free, go to angieslist.com today.
- Fact, we all love video doorbells.
- [Man] Voice assistants
have changed our lives.
- We now control our home with a touch.
And you now what's better
than all these things by themselves?
- All these things combined.
- From the most trusted name in security.
- [Both] ADT.
(upbeat rock music)
- [Announcer] Want the look of extensions
with the ease of mascara?
You need Lash Ease,
mascara that gives you
an instant lash lift.
It virtually doubles the
length of your lashes
in just one step.
- I just discovered this
new mascara, Lash Ease,
and it is crazy.
- Look at the difference
between these two.
Lash Ease is amazing.
- [Announcer] Get Lash
Ease for only $19.99.
Available online and at
these fine retailers.
- The best way to hit the beach?
With Neutrogena Beach Defense sunscreen.
Helioplex-powered, UVA/UVB strong.
Beach-strength protection
for the whole family.
For the best day in the sun.
Neutrogena.
- I found a way to relieve my constipation
that's both gentle and fast.
- [Announcer] New Dulcolax
Liquid works naturally
with the water in my body
to provide gentle relief
in as little as 30 minutes.
New stimulant-free Dulcolax Li--
- [Announcer] Attention
Medicare beneficiaries.
The Center for Medicare Services
has officially authorized new benefits
Medicare Advantage plans may include.
Plans may now include private home aides
and rides to medical appointments.
Most plans also include dental, vision,
hearing, and prescription drug coverage.
To get the benefits you deserve,
call the Medicare Coverage Helpline now.
- Hi, I'm Joe Namath.
I called the Medicare Coverage Helpline
and they instantly advised me
that I wasn't getting all
the benefits I deserve.
They explained I could get a plan
that includes dental and
prescription coverage,
as well as the new coverage
for private home aides
and rides to medical appointments.
If you wanna find out what you deserve,
call the number on your screen now.
It's free!
You'll be happy you
called, I guarantee it.
- [Announcer] Call to
see if you can save money
and get more benefits now.
Don't delay, call now.
It's free.
Call 1-800-989-3300.
That's 1-800-989-3300 now.
- [Announcer] Stop paying too
much for your prescriptions.
- That wraps up this hour.
I'm Chris Jansing, in for Stephanie Ruhle.
Coming up right now, more
news with Hallie Jackson.
Hey, Hallie.
- Hey, Chris,
thank you so much.
On this holiday Wednesday,
we've got breaking news out
of the Trump Administration.
A new investigation ordered by DHS
into those reports about Border
Patrol agents and the dist--