- Defined branding for us in the modern.
- None of us knew what that swoosh
was until they invented it.
- Of marketing, yeah!
And signing Kaepernick you know,
in those moments where
there was a lot criticism
which they knew they were going to get,
the burning of the shoes
and the rest of it.
In those immediate moments after that,
they did actually see
their stock price go up
- [Man] Yeah.
and their shoes sales go up.
- It'll be interesting
to see what happens now
and whether their reaction
to this controversy
was the right step.
- Alright, Stephanie
thanks for covering for us.
Stephanie Gosk, NBC correspondent.
Thanks for watching.
Oh, look at that!
We're out of time.
Thanks for watching Velshi and Ruhle,
see you back here at 3:00 p.m. Eastern.
I'll also be back at 11:00 p.m. Eastern.
Check us out on social media,
connect with our show at velshiruhle.
Kasie Hunt picks up
our coverage right now.
Hello, friend!
- Hello to you as well, Ali.
And we will see you of
course in just an hour.
Good afternoon,
I am Kasie Hunt in for Katy Tur.
It's 11:00 a.m. out west and
2:00 p.m. here in Washington,
where the President's own
Department of Homeland Security
has issued a scathing report
on the squalid conditions
found in a number of migrant
detention centers along the border.
The report from the DHS's
Office of the Inspector General
describes dangerous levels of overcrowding
for long periods of time.
In one facility,
some adults were kept in
standing room only conditions
for a week.
While at another,
many migrants spent more
than a month in small cells
packed dangerously over capacity.
Most of the adults have not had a shower,
despite some of them being
held for as long as a month.
Some facilities provided wet
wipes to maintain hygiene.
One man, locked in a crowded cells,
held up a crudely-made
sign for inspectors,
begging for help.
Meanwhile, many children
were held without care
for basic standards of living,
including access to
showers and clean clothes.
At two of the five facilities visited
by the Inspector General,
children were not given hot meals
until the inspectors arrived.
But according to the
President and his allies,
there's nothing to see here.
Just ask acting DHS head Kevin McAleenan,
who defended the
conditions at one notorious
Texas detention center late last week.
- Unsubstantiated allegations
last week regarding
a single border control facility
in Clint Station in Texas
created a sensation,
that's balanced somewhat
since several media outlets
toured the Clint Station and saw
the actual conditions there.
A clean and well-managed facility
and well-equipped process,
but frankly much of the
coverage is simply too late
and is missing the story.
- So, our big question today is:
will the White House accept accountability
for its immigration policies?
Joining me now NBC News
correspondent Jacob Soboroff,
former Republican Congressman
and MSNBC political
analyst Carlos Curbelo,
and former California
Senator Barbara Boxer,
she now hosts the Boxer podcast.
Jacob, let me start with you.
This report from the OIG,
I'm just gonna read a
little bit more from it.
Senior managers at several facilities
raised security concerns for
their agents and the detainees.
For example, one called the
situation "a ticking time bomb."
It really underscores
the fact that they seem
to have understood just
how bad things had gotten
and just how much of a
problem this was gonna be
and yet, nothing seems to be done.
- Yeah, you hit the
nail on the head, Kasie.
And I think the ticking
time bomb very clearly
references and is an
accurate description of these
seven facilities in the Rio Gran valley,
but not only there.
It can be applied to the
facilities that Julia Ainsley
and I reported on earlier this
week in the Al Paso sector.
And frankly, that phrase,
"a ticking time bomb"
can be ascribed to the border
patrol detention system
that has existed in this
country for decades.
It has never been worse
than it is right now during
the Trump Administration,
seeing more families come
here than ever before,
particularly because of the
aggressive metering policies
and the remain in Mexico
policies that are forcing people
to cross illegally because
they don't want to wait
in one of the most dangerous
countries in the world, Mexico.
But for years we have known
that those detention facilities
are designed for single adult men
and as you have people that
are coming to claim asylum,
unaccompanied minors,
we saw this during the Obama
Administration in 2014,
and now families during
the Trump Administration,
those facilities are not
suitable for the people
that we are seeing cross our border,
largely asylum seekers.
So you could call them a ticking time bomb
over the course of the last year,
but frankly they've
been a ticking time bomb
for decades, Kasie.
- Jacob, the White House
must have had advanced notice
of this report, no?
- You know, I don't know that
the White House specifically,
I have no reporting that the
White House had knowledge
of what was going on in
these facilities and what the
Office of Inspector General
in the Department of Homeland
Security was finding.
But they certainly have
had access to conversations
with members of the Department
of Homeland Security.
They've known about, and
I'm sure the President
is getting reports on who
is crossing the border,
where these folks are being detained,
ultimately where they want to go
and why they come to this country.
So the idea that maybe this is a surprise
to the White House doesn't
square with the information
that's available to them from their own
Department of Homeland Security.
I know that they are very,
very plugged in to what's
going on on a daily basis
down there on the border.
- Yeah, Congressman Curbelo,
you had visited and been,
or tried to visit, I should say,
visit a detention facility
and were denied access
when you were a member of Congress.
And you are Republican,
albeit one who has advocated
at times for an immigration
policy that is different
than what this administration
has obviously pushed.
What is your view on
what the administration
needs to be doing right
now to help the people
who are in these detention centers?
- Well Kasie, first let
me say that this would be
a difficult situation
for any administration.
On any given day, three,
four, five thousand
people are coming across the border.
This is a new kind of immigration,
not the kind that we used
to see 10, 15 years ago.
A lot of families, a
lot of young children.
This is a difficult challenge
and I think we have to be fair
and have to recognize that.
The other thing I'll say is
that there's a major difference
between the detention
facilities near the border
and those in other parts of the country.
Down here in South Florida
there are a few of them
dedicated specifically to minors
and the conditions there are a lot better
than what we see out of those
images coming from the border.
But the fact remains
that the administration
has to do better and that
they would just brush off
this report from the IG
at the Department of Homeland
Security is unacceptable.
Congress has to do more
to dedicate more funding
to update these facilities to make sure
that they're compatible
with the kind of immigration
we're seeing coming into our country.
And of course, the laws
do have to be changed
because unfortunately the
way our laws are designed,
they do invite people to
come over with children
specifically because the
Coyotes advertise that
as a more advantageous strategy for trying
to come to the United States.
So this is a complex, complicated problem
and unfortunately I don't
think this White House
is taking it as seriously as they should.
- Senator Boxer, there is though,
I mean I take the Congressman's point,
but there are still a
lot of decisions that any
administration can make about
how they are going to
prioritize the enforcements
of our laws based on the
records of the people
that are crossing our borders.
What could the Trump
Administration be doing differently
today to try to make this better?
- Listen, I'm gonna talk
in very stark terms here.
What we see is not a ticking time bomb.
The bomb has gone off for
seven children who died,
for these little babies
that have blue fingers
because they're freezing,
these parents who were told, reportedly,
drink out of the toilet
because there's no fresh water.
This is not "you have to do better" time,
this is "we're not going to have this
done in our name" time.
And we have to fix it.
It's a stain on America,
it's being done in our name.
So, what do we do?
The first thing is we bring
back the model project
that Barack Obama had in
place that worked very well
as an alternative to detention
where 98% of the people
showed up for their court date.
Secondly, we need a surge of case workers.
Beto O'rourke has suggested this.
Case workers for these various cases
they can be followed so
they follow the rules,
and they are taken care of.
And we know that this deterance
is a strategy of Trump
and how does he think
he's gonna deter people?
By making them go through agony.
This is not America!
It needs to stop.
Period.
- Jacob Soboroff, jump in.
- Yeah, so respectively
to both the Senator
and the Congressman,
both of you served when these facilities
were already in place.
In 2014, President Obama
had a surge of unaccompanied
migrant children in
facilities just like this
and we saw pictures just like this.
And so these conditions are not new,
so I do agree with you, Senator Boxer,
that President Trump has made
this worse than ever before,
and Congressman Curbelo,
I have been to that homestead
facility in South Florida,
I was just there last
week during the debates
where 2,300 migrant children
are currently living
in the custody of HHS,
and yes, certainly, the
facilities there are better,
and there are licensed social care workers
to take care of the children.
But the idea that we didn't
have any warning of this,
that the ticking time bomb is just limited
to this time period now,
I don't think it's fair.
I mean I think that the idea
that the immigration detention
system has largely been
based on deterrence
since the Clinton Administration,
there was an official document
that the border patrol
put out called, "Prevention
through Deterrence,"
they've known that
deterrence-based model from
the Clinton Administration
into the Bush Administration,
into the Obama Administration,
and now with the Trump
Administration worse than
ever before, was always forcing people
to take more dangerous and
deadly routes into this country.
And that the conditions
that they were housed in
once they were in
detention were never meant
to be for people to stay over 72 hours,
and we have seen stuff like this before,
it's just not as bad as it is today.
- Could I respond to that
- [Kasie] Senator Boxer,
yeah please, I mean,
- since I was mentioned?
- The reality here is that the
Obama Administration's record
on immigration has in
fact been criticized,
partly for the reasons
that Jacob outlines.
Your response.
- It's all fine, it's all fine.
The bottom line is, we
can look back to that days
where there were these issues,
but I would argue there was
nothing, nothing to this extent.
This is now deterrence by agony.
That's what we have.
It's just unreal,
and I voted for comprehensive
immigration reform,
had Paul Ryan allowed
that to go to a vote,
we wouldn't have any of this now.
So we can argue about
what happened in 2014,
I'm up for that.
I'm not absolving anybody.
What I'm saying is,
this is happening now.
Let's fix it now.
- [Kasie] Right.
- Let's search the judges,
let's search the case workers,
let's go back to Obama's
plan which was an alternative
to detention that Jake didn't mention
that was working really well.
Let's try it, I don't care,
I'm not saying everyone
has been wonderful on this,
I'm not saying I've
been wonderful on this,
it's happening now.
And I'll tell you something.
I wouldn't be surprised if
there's some kind of complaint
to the World Court about this,
that there are crimes
- Kasie.
- against humanity going on
in our name, in our name.
- [Kasie] Congressman jump in.
- Let me just say briefly,
the administration deserves
a lot of the criticism
it receives and certainly on immigration.
I was an outspoken critic
when I was at Congress
of this administration,
but I will say,
we need a little sobriety here.
We need to take note of the fact
that this is an extraordinary
set of circumstances.
I remember in 1994 when
over 30,000 Cubans attempted
to come across the Florida straits,
the Clinton Administration
set up tent cities
in Guantanamo Bay, at Gitmo.
We are seeing a flood of
immigrants, of migrants
coming across the border
that is extraordinary
and that doesn't mean it's
acceptable for the conditions
that have been reported
out of these facilities
to be present,
that all has to change.
But again, this is not a
regular time when it comes
to illegal immigration into our country
and we just simply have
to take that into account
in evaluating what's
happening at the border.
- But don't you think, Congressman,
I mean I do take your point
that this is an extraordinary
circumstance but I mean
these people are suffering
as the Senator said,
in our name right now.
- And that's totally
unacceptable and what we need
is for Congress to fund new
facilities that are compatible,
the type of immigration we're
getting into our country.
It's not men crossing the
border looking for work anymore,
it's families, it's children,
and these facilities aren't
designed to hold them.
And we need facilities that
can hold these families
while their cases are adjudicated,
while they're being processed.
Clearly, we don't have that in place today
and that has to change.
- Sorry, Kasie, can I
just quickly jump in?
- Very quickly, Jacob, last
word we gotta go to break.
- Sure, just what the
Congressman is suggesting here,
and correct me if I'm wrong, Congressman,
is what the Trump
Administration is suggesting
and what the Obama
Administration also wanted to do,
which was to turn around
unaccompanied, undocumented
migrant children from Central
America and deport them
immediately when they get here,
and or detain families indefinitely,
indefinite detention of migrant families,
instead of releasing
them into the interior.
I think it's a very controversial policy,
and when you say we
need to change the laws,
I think we need to go a
little deeper on what changing
those laws actually
means and what that means
for the migrants
- Well, Jacob.
that we're saying right
now that we want to help.
- Real quick, it doesn't
have to be that way.
We can prioritize cases
where minors are involved
so that they can be processed immediately,
not so that they're held
for months and months
but maybe two, three weeks
until those cases are adjudicated.
- This is obviously
- And can I just say.
an incredibly, I'm sorry Senator
we're gonna have to,
- Can I just jump in here too.
This is clearly
- Well, why don't we
- very emotional.
- help those countries?
- This is a very emotional
- No, it is.
debate and that is absolutely a policy
that we also have
discussed on this program
and will in the future.
Jacob Soboroff, Carlos
Curbelo and Barbara Boxer,
thank you all very much.
- Still to come this hour,
new concerns just hours before
the Fourth of July
celebration in Washington,
including reports that
only Trump supporters
will get a front row seat
to the President's salute to America.
Plus, Iowa, Iowa, Iowa.
Kamala Harris heads to
the first caucus state
using her post-debate surge in polling
to close the gap on
front-runner Joe Biden.
Right after this break,
why the President's campaign
is reportedly concerned
that it may not have a major tool
in its political arsenal come 2020.
(low drum beat)
- As you now have 76,000 points,
as part of the loyalty program,
there's a 5% discount
applied to your hotel room.
$120 for the night, please.
- Oh, 5% off as well
as free Wi-Fi, not bad.
- $95 for the night, please sir.
- Wait, wait what?
- If you use Trivago,
Trivago will compare hotel prices
from hundreds of websites worldwide.
So you can often find a better
deal for your hotel room.
And also free Wi-Fi.
Maybe you should try Trivago next time.
- [Narrator] Hotel? Trivago.
- I found a way to relieve my constipation
that's both gentle and fast.
New Dulcolax liquid works
naturally with the water
in my body to provide gentle relief
in as little as 30 minutes.
New stimulant free Dulcolax liquid.
Puts you comfortably in control.
- [Narrator] Thanks, Golden Corral.
Dan gets his slow-smoked sirloin.
And my little trio are as happy as shrimp!
Oops, clams.
And mom, got it all.
Hook, line and sirloin.
The slow-smoked sirloin and shrimp trio.
Golden Corral, the only one for everyone.
- Hi, I'm Dana Loesch from the Dana show.
If you could be more heart-healthy,
just by drinking a glass of
earthy vegetable juice daily,
would you do it?
Probably not.
But what if this
performance enhancing veggie
was transformed into a great tasting
circulation super food drink?
It's called Super Beets.
And I can help you try it risk-free.
See, Super Beets helps boost
your body's nitric oxide levels.
And that helps increase
your energy and stamina.
It supports healthy blood pressure, too.
I drink Super Beets in
the morning for energy,
at the gym for extra long workouts,
in the afternoon as a pick-me-up
without jittery side effects.
Get a bonus 30 day supply
free with your first order.
Plus, get the book Beet the
Odds free and free shipping too.
It's guaranteed or you're
gonna get your money back.
You'll love it.
- I immediately felt like
I was 10 years younger.
- Within 30 minutes of taking it,
I felt a difference.
- [Narrator] Call 1.800.409.0284
or go to superbeets.
- If you bought a
timeshare for your family,
by now you've learned the ugly truth.
Timeshares are the only
thing that you can buy
that you don't know how
much it's going to cost
or when it's gonna end.
It's like giving them a blank check
for annual maintenance
and assessment fees.
Sounds crazy, right?
The ugly truth is that this never ends.
Even when you die,
your family will be
stuck with this burden.
Hello, I'm Chuck McDowell
and 10 years ago I founded
Wesley Financial Group
with one goal in mind:
helping good folks just like you
cancel their timeshare contract.
And what that means for
you and your family:
No more mortgage payments,
no more maintenance fee surprises,
and no more timeshare.
So call today.
The call is free, the
information kit is free,
and I guarantee if we can't
cancel your timeshare contract,
you'll pay nothing.
- [Announcer] You can legally
get out of your timeshare.
For your free information
kit explaining how,
call 800-395-8811.
- [Chuck] You save.
(Quick beat)
- How do you learn how
to run when you've never
done anything remotely like this before?
- We're prepared to do it in a novel way,
in an original way.
And we wanna make sure that
we're writing our own playbook.
Do you think that we should
keep troops in Afghanistan?
- I do not and I believe
that we need to do it though,
in a responsible way.
(upbeat drums)
- Where do you see your party right now?
- It's going to be how do we
think government should work
and who do we think
government should work for?
(upbeat drums)
(techno beat)
- The Trump Administration is
reportedly sweating bullets
over what some are
describing as a meltdown
at the National Rifle Association.
Politico reporting today quote:
"The turmoil is fueling
fears that the organization
will be profoundly diminished
heading into the election,
leaving the Republic
Party with a gaping hole
in its political machinery."
The President called the NRA a quote,
"victim of harassment"
in a tweet this week
saying that the gun
rights group that helped
get him to the White
House might move to Texas,
where they are loved.
He suggested the NRA can
get better protection there
from the New York state investigation
into the group's tax exempt status.
But the attention from the President
comes amid multiple other
reports around the fracture
at the NRA including an ugly dispute
over leadership of the organization.
Joining me now, Politico
political reporter Alex Isenstadt
and Daily Beast politics reporter
and MSNBC contributor Betsy Woodruff.
Thank you both for being here.
Alex, this was your story
in Politico about just how
concerned the President's
campaign is about,
frankly it seems like a
total collapse at the NRA
or at least an inability to
look outward at this point.
What does it mean potentially
for the President's reelect?
- It's hard to overstate
just how important
the NRA is to the Republican Party
turn-out apparatus in elections.
The NRA has over 5 million
members and the dues-paying
members they do have,
for them the NRA is a very important,
it's a very important organization
and so they can really turn out voters
and they can turn out voters
for the Republican side.
And so without them on the field,
that could have big implications
for the GOP come 2020.
- Betsy, you've done a lot
of reporting on kind of how
the bottom has fallen out of the NRA
and kind of how they've
all turned on each other.
What is your assessment
rooted in that reporting,
of how effective the NRA
is going to be capable
of being in 2020?
- The biggest question is just money.
Is the NRA going to be able
to replicate the massive
expenditures that it made
on Trump's race in 2016.
Remember, in 2016 it
was fairly controversial
within the NRA as to whether
to spend as much money
as they did on Trump.
There were some voices
according to my sources
who said this Trump guy doesn't look like
he's gonna go very far,
maybe we should focus on Congress,
making sure the potential
President Clinton
wouldn't have majorities
in the House and Senate.
But several important
leadership figures in the NRA
including, according to
people I've spoken to,
Chris Cox argued no,
we need to go all in and we
need to spend big on Trump.
Chris Cox, who used to be
the top lobbyist at the NRA
just officially left the association
within the last few days.
How that leadership void
is going to be filled
is really important.
And of course the huge question is just,
are the NRA's financial
problems gonna limit
how big of a war chest they
have to spend on Trump?
Oliver North, who was
formerly president of the NRA
deposed and what some described as a coo,
wrote in a document that I obtained
that the NRA's outside counsel had billed
at upwards of 24 million
dollars over about a year
just for legal services.
Now that number is disputed by some,
but if they're spending on
legal bills at that scale,
that's a lot of money for a non-profit
and it's money they can't spend in 2020.
- And Betsy is this,
how much of this has trickled
down to the NRA's members
that Alex was talking about?
I mean are people starting
who normally give money,
show up, do what the NRA asks them to do,
are they starting to get nervous?
- Look, it's hard to say exactly
how far it's trickled out.
And remember among the
NRA's core membership
there's a lot of skepticism
of the mainstream media.
They view a lot of the
reporters who cover these issues
as fundamentally hostile to the
things that they care about.
So as far as an audience,
in terms of the way they
relate to news reports,
it's more skeptical.
That said, at the same time,
of course it is affecting the membership,
it's frustrating board members,
Allen West who's sort of a
conservative fan favorite
is a member of the NRA
board and has called
for Wayne LaPierre to be deposed.
And frankly, if you
just look at the debates
that are going on,
on NRA board member's Facebook pages
and in the YouTube comments
of gun YouTube pages,
you'll see a ton of friction
and a ton of criticism
particularly of NRA's CEO Wayne LaPierre.
- And Alex, you also write
in your story that this goes,
the concern about this
goes beyond the President,
that some Republicans
are calling on the NRA
to address its 2020 plans and
that within the past week,
senators have privately expressed
concerns about the group
to NRSC Chairman Todd Young.
I mean this could really affect
the Senate playing field, too.
- Absolutely, Senate,
the Republicans are trying to
protect their Senate majority
in 2020 and a lot of these Senators
who were elected first in 2014,
they won with the help of the
National Rifle Association.
And so you can be that
it's not just going to be
the Trump campaign that's
gonna be counting on the NRA
to turn out voters in critical states
like Michigan, Pennsylvania, Wisconsin,
those really important Rust Belt.
It's also gonna be Senators who are up
for reelection in 2020 and
so you're likely to hear
a lot more from them in
the weeks to come on this.
- [Kasie] Alright, a lot at stake here.
Alex Isenstadt, Betsy Woodruff,
thank you guys both very much,
it's great to see you.
With her polling on the rise,
can Kamala Harris create
a winning coalition
like former President Obama's?
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] After a week of epic stories,
Donny Deutsch separates
the news from the noise.
Bringing his branding
instincts to politics,
and breaking down the key
strategies heading into 2020.
Saturday Night Politics
with Donny Deutsch.
Saturdays at 8:00, MSNBC.
- Most homeowners draw a blank when asked
what they're home projects should cost.
That's why at HomeAdvisor,
you can see what other's paid
for similar jobs in your area.
Start your next home project
knowing what you should pay.
Go to HomeAdvisor.com or
download the free app.
- [Announcer] If you have moderate
to severe psoriasis or
psoriatic arthritis,
little things can be a big deal.
That's why there's Otezla.
Otezla is not an injection or a cream.
It's a pill that treats differently.
For psoriasis, 75%
clearer skin is achievable
with reduced redness, thickness,
and scaliness of plaques.
For psoriatic arthritis,
Otezla is proven to reduce
joint swelling, tenderness and pain.
And the Otezla prescribing
information has no requirement
for routine lab monitoring.
Don't use if you're allergic to Otezla.
It may cause severe diarrhea,
nausea, or vomiting.
Otezla is associated with an
increased risk of depression.
Tell your doctor if you
have a history of depression
or suicidal thoughts or
if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor your weight
and may stop treatment.
Upper respiratory tract
infection and headache may occur.
Tell your doctor about your medicines
and if you're pregnant or planning to be.
Ready to treat differently with a pill?
Otezla: show more of you.
- [Announcer] Instead of
going to school every morning,
what if school could come to you?
Because learning happens
anywhere and everywhere.
K12 powered schools
provided a tuition-free,
full-time online public school education
- It's public school at home.
- [Narrator] Visit K12.com to learn more.
- My students are ready
to accept the challenge,
and they get all the
attention that they deserve.
- [Announcer] Students benefit
from personalized support
from state-certified teachers.
- That to me is like
a huge support for me.
Honestly she's just happier.
- I can have more time with
my family and do gymnastics.
- [Announcer] K12's curriculum is designed
to engage students,
to challenge them,
and it's tuition-free.
- It's been a huge change
in her life and ours.
- [Announcer] So visit K12.com today.
And join the over one
million K12 students who have
chosen public school at home.
Tuition-free and available in most states.
- [Announcer] Constipation
can happen all around us.
You just need to know where to look.
(soft upbeat jazz music)
Luckily, there's Colace.
It's the number one doctor
recommended stool-softener brand.
- Can't sleep?
Do ransomware and cyber
threats make you toss and turn?
You don't need a new pillow,
you need PC Matic.
Hello, I'm Rob Cheng, CEO
and founder of PC Matic.
My wife was infected
with an early ransomware,
causing many sleepless nights.
So we built a whitelist antivirus
to block all viruses including ransomware.
Giving your family the sleep they deserve.
The viruses are made off-shore
and so is every other antivirus.
Only PC Matic is made in America.
Learn about the dangers of cyberspace.
PC Matic includes security
awareness training.
Computer slow?
Your PC's will wake up ready to go
with PC Matic's automated maintenance.
PC Matic is a great deal at just $50
for five computers for one year.
Skeptical? PC Matic has
a full no questions asked
money back guarantee.
Still not sure?
Cyber Defense Magazine named PC Matic
most innovated antivirus for 2018.
Go to PCMatic.com and sleep well.
- [Narrator] Never go to
the Post Office again.
(soft techno beat)
- After a stand-out debate performance,
Senator Kamala Harris will
campaign in Iowa today.
It's a place where support
for the California candidate
appears to be surging,
according to several post-debate polls.
A new USA Today Suffolk University poll
puts Harris in second place with 16%
in the early caucus state.
The Senator's rise has some wondering
whether she can follow in
President Obama's footsteps.
As NBC's Alex Seitz-Wald puts it,
quote, "The question turns to
the notion of electability-
an obsession for many
Democratic primary voters-
on its head,
and would have been
inconceivable just a week ago.
Like Obama, Harris hails from
her party's establishment,
but is a relatively fresh
face with only two years under
her belt in the Senate.
And she has some progressive positions
that could also make her
appealing to younger,
more liberal voters."
Joining me now from Iowa,
NBC News political
reporter Vaughn Hillyard,
reporter for NBCnews.com Alex Seitz-Wald,
and PBS News Hour Washington correspondent
and an MSNBC political
contributor, Yamiche Alcindor.
Vaughn, let me start
with you on the ground.
Obviously these polls have
been good for Senator Harris,
but I'm curious what you're
picking up behind the scenes
with the campaign.
I mean clearly many of her staffers
have been pretty giddy
about that performance
and it is starting to
show up in the numbers,
but at the same time,
they've made a risky strategy bet here,
and there are also questions
if she is gonna go all in in Iowa,
this poll would suggest perhaps she can.
What are you picking up on?
- Exactly, this is a campaign
that looked at their polling
sitting at about 6, 7, 8%.
Ever since her launch back in January,
and the campaign always
looked at this as the debate
being the opportunity
to introduce herself,
as Alex pointed out in his piece there,
she's just in her third year
in the United States
Senate out of California.
The debate was an opportunity
to speak before 20 million people
and essentially introduce herself.
And what this campaign has felt compelled
to make the case on,
from going from the likes of Michigan,
down into Louisiana,
through this primary process,
is that Kamala Harris is a
general election candidate.
Well, Barack Obama won,
we should know, back in 2008,
won the Iowa caucus over the likes
of John Edwards and Hillary Clinton.
He also won the state of Iowa
over not only John McCain in 2008
but also Mitt Romney in 2012.
That was the state of Iowa.
And they make the case,
if Kamala Harris can go into
places like here in Iowa
but also up in Michigan
and drive higher turn-out
in places like the Detroit area,
or around the parts of Milwaukee,
essentially when you're
talking about electability,
Kamala Harris is your
candidate and that's the case
that now she's trying to
make here over the course
of these next three days
in Iowans, into Iowans.
- Yamiche Alcindor what have
you seen on this question
of Iowa and,
it's true that Barack Obama
was an African American
who appealed to a largely
white electorate in Iowa and
it's what set him on the path
to the Presidency,
and the coalition that
we're starting to see behind
some of this polling is white liberals
and increasingly African Americans.
Is this a trajectory that can hold?
- It's a trajectory that can hold for now
if she can weather the
storm of what will now be
an intense look at her background,
an intense vetting of her stances
on all sorts of things as a prosecutor.
I think, I've talked to
some Democratic consultants
who say there's gonna be
a number of front runners
going forward so right now Joe
Biden was seen as the person
that was really leading the pack,
now after this debate, Kamala Harris,
Elizabeth Warren I should also say,
are on the rise.
But I think what we're
really gonna have to look at
is whether or not after
people learn more about
Senator Harris' background including
all her criminal justice issues,
but also her stances
on all sorts of things
including immigration and health care,
where she differs in some
ways from other candidates.
Thinking about the fact that
she said that she would not
leave private insurance or
eliminate private insurance
for government-run insurance.
So I think once people really
start digging into her,
we'll really have to see whether or not
she can hold that coalition together.
But of course, people are
very excited about her.
I think her debate performance
really made a lot of people
think she could go after Donald Trump,
be on stage with him,
look him in the eye and
really go toe-to-toe with him.
- So Alex, one critical
piece here obviously
is African American voters.
And that has been the most important,
if I would say piece to
Joe Biden's support so far.
And you write, "Support
for Biden among blacks,
a critical Democratic voting bloc,
was cut in half."
You're talking about one of these,
oh, excuse me this is a Reuter's poll,
not your story, my apologies.
But they're writing with two out of 10
saying they backed Obama's
former vice president,
compared with four out of 10
in the June poll for Biden.
So I mean Harris does seem to
be making real in-roads here.
What's going to cement this
coalition, if anything?
- Right, well this is the
promise of the Kamala Harris
candidacy from the very
beginning that a candidate
with her background could
unite white liberals,
Whole Foods liberals in one hand,
and of course African Americans.
- [Kasie] Whole Foods liberals, yes.
(laughs)
- Given her background,
those two groups together,
the Whole Foods liberals
and African Americans,
that's a pretty unstoppable coalition
in a Democratic primary.
Of course that didn't
happen until the debate.
But there's now been
about four or five polls
that have come after the debate
including the Reuter's poll,
there's a Quinnipiac poll yesterday
that showed her climbing
among African Americans
and Biden falling.
And as you said,
that has been his biggest
source of strength,
it was Hillary Clinton's biggest
source of strength in 2016.
I think the field is probably
too big for any one candidate
to consolidate African Americans.
Cory Booker is obviously
still in this race.
But if she can solidify
a big chunk of them,
that can create a base
for her in the long run.
And she has a huge amount of room to grow.
She can appeal to African Americans,
she can appeal to white liberals,
she's also Indian American
and she's a woman.
Women did very well in 2018.
Democrats are very excited
about the idea of voting
for women right now.
The question is, is she
too little to everyone
and kinda fall in the middle,
which is I think where she has
been heading into the debate,
or can she now use the
strength of the debate stage
to press forward and solidify that count.
- Let me flip that last point you made
about women voter's on its head
because I'm curious how much
you're picking up on this.
Lisa Lara over at the New
York Times wrote today
about the thinking that
a woman is not the right
nominee in 2016 because
a woman, or in 2020,
because a woman lost to
Donald Trump in 2016.
And there was a South Carolina
voter quoted in her story,
who supports Harris,
but this woman who says she
is an African American woman
says quote, "I don't think she can win.
And I'm sorry to have to say that.
She is a woman and she is black.
As a black woman myself,
I think that as much as
we would like to believe
there's been this huge
shift in this country,
we have seen the reality
that people will fight
back against change."
How much has this sentiment under
the radar that it often is,
contributed to Harris' struggle to rise?
Clearly she's broken out since,
but she was kinda floating
back there for a while.
Is this why?
- I think this is a huge problem
for her and Elizabeth Warren.
Electability is the number
one thing that Democrats
say they care about this year.
The very first voter
that I talked to in Iowa
of this entire year,
January 6th at an Elizabeth Warren event,
said, "I love Elizabeth
Warren, but I don't think
the country is ready for a woman."
It was a middle-aged
woman who told me that.
So this is a very real phenomenon.
The data, on the other hand,
show that this absolutely not true,
that women when they're on the ballot
win just as often as men do,
that there is no punishment
for electability,
and that the under representation
of women in politics
is more about barriers
entry for candidates getting
on the ballots more than
voters discriminating
against them when they're voting.
So I think the electorate
is starting to realize that,
but it's going to take some
time to combat the perception
that they're not electable.
- Of course the question
- [Yamiche] I also think
Barack Obama.
- is what is the
difference between, the
difference of course
between the data that you're talking about
and what actually is
playing out on the ground
is something that we've
never had it tested
at the Presidential level.
- [Alex] True.
- And I'm sorry Yamiche, go ahead.
- Well I'll also just say
that when Barack Obama
was running there were
so many African Americans
that told me personally,
"I'm not sure that this
country's ready for it,"
but then when he won Iowa,
and he started really
showing off in the debates
and people really started
listening to his message
and became really
inspired by his campaign,
people put all that aside and said
"We're gonna go behind
this African American man."
So I think same thing with Senator Harris,
I think her debate performance made people
think she might be capable of doing this
and start really helping people understand
that there can be an
African American woman.
So I think, and when we
saw progress last time
it was an African American
man pushing the boundaries
and we can say that again.
I think if we see that,
it will be Elizabeth
Warren or Tulsi Gabbard,
or other women possibly
pushing the cards to say,
look we can do this and
we can inspire a nation,
if they are to be successful.
- Alright, Yamiche Alcindor,
Alex Sietz-Wald, Vaugh Hillyard,
thank you guys all very much.
So with Biden in the lead and
Harris surging in these polls,
what about the rest of the field?
We're gonna check in
with NBC's road warriors
who are with Senators Sanders and Warren,
coming up next.
(slow drum music)
(alarm beeping)
- [Narrator] Wake up.
There's a lot that
needs to get done today.
(bright upbeat music)
Small things, big things.
Too hard to do alone things.
Day after day, you need
to get it all done.
And here to listen and
help you through it all
is Bank of America.
With the expertise and know-how you need,
to reach that blissful state of doneness.
So let's get after it.
What would you like the power to do?
- [Announcer] If you
are over the age of 50
and considering buying an
annuity in the next 60 days,
I have some important news for you.
Don't buy an annuity until you understand
the pros and cons of annuities.
A free book to help you
maximize your retirement income
from television host and three-time author
Josh Mellberg has been released.
This book reveals little known truths
about annuity strategies in
simple to understand terms.
Grab a pen right now because
we are about to offer you
this free book that unlocks
the five little known secrets
we believe baby boomers
and seniors should know
before buying an annuity.
Call 800-721-5959 now and
you'll receive a free copy
of Josh Mellberg's book NextGen
Annuity Strategies Revealed.
As a bonus, we'll also send
you the #1 Mistake Retirees
are Making with their Investments Today.
And a free DVD on how you can get
up to 33% more income in retirement.
Call 800-721-5959.
Again that's 800-721-5959.
(Upbeat music)
♪ Na, na, na na ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
- [Announcer] The world's
first six function
multi-pro tailgate.
Available only on the next
generation GMC Sierra.
Get 20% below MSRP on next
generation 2019 GMC double cab
and SLE crew cab models
with a standard tailgate.
- I'm Alex Trebek here to tell you
about the Colonial Penn Program.
If you're age 50 to 85 and
looking to buy life insurance
on a fixed budget,
remember the three P's.
- What are the three P's?
- The three P's of life
insurance on a fixed budget
are Price, Price, and Price.
A price you can afford,
a price that can't increase,
and a price that fits your budget.
- I'm 65 and take medications.
What's my price?
You can get coverage for $9.95 a month.
- I just turned 80.
What's my price?
- $9.95 a month for you, too.
If you're aged 50-85,
call now about the number one
most popular whole life insurance plan.
Available through the
Colonial Penn Program.
It has an affordable rate
starting at $9.95 a month.
No medical exam, no health questions.
Your acceptance is guaranteed.
And this plan has a
guaranteed lifetime rate-lock.
So your rate can never
go up for any reason.
And with this plan, you
can pick your payment date,
so you can time your premium due date
to work with your budget.
So call now for free information.
And you'll also get this
free beneficiary planner.
And it's yours just for calling.
So call now.
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-775-7230
for your free information
and your free gift.
That number again is 1-800-775-7230.
Call now.
(soft techno music)
- Vice President Joe Biden is still atop
every poll out there,
and yes, caveat, it is early.
But according to three major
polls out since the debates,
a field of four: Biden,
Harris, Warren and Sanders
seem to be separating from the pack.
And when Quinnipiac asked
specifically about which
candidate had the best policy ideas,
two of those contenders came
out as clear-cut favorites:
Senators Elizabeth Warren
and Bernie Sanders.
Covering their campaigns
and joining me now,
NBC News political
reporters Shaquille Brewster
and Ali Vitali and here
with me in Washington,
Reuter's political
correspondent, Ginger Gibson.
Shaq, let me start with you
because Sander's support
has been slipping in these
recent national polls
and I've seen some flashes of frustration
from Sanders in that he
feels and will tell anyone,
well, told me in a recent interview,
he's the person, he's the
reason why we're talking about
so many of these policy issues,
Medicare for all, et cetera,
how is the campaign trying
to get their footing back underneath them?
- You hit that point, Kasie,
there are so many more options for voters
in this election with so
many candidates there.
And that's why you have Senator
Sanders trying to really
focus on contacting as
many voters as they can.
He's in the middle of this three day swing
through the state of Iowa.
And what's different about this swing
is what he's highlighting in this trip.
And I can tell you he's not
highlighting those recent polls
and I spoke to his chief of
staff just about an hour ago
and for every poll I was
able to mention where Sanders
was apparently losing
support or losing ground
or ticking down in the polls,
he was able to throw back
polls that showed him
either gaining support or stagnant.
So that's why Sanders is here,
he's focused on retail politics.
He's having ice cream socials,
he's gonna be marching in several,
I believe it's five
Independence Day parades
over the course of this trip.
He's trying to connect with
as many voters as he can
and then he's also focused
on his ground game.
He just opened up an
office here in Iowa City,
he's gonna be opening up
two more on this trip,
trying to galvanize his supporters
and bring in as many volunteers as he can.
He wants to show that he
still has that momentum
that he had in 2016
through his supporters.
- Well that organization
I will absolutely buy
but I do not recognize the
ice cream social candidate
Bernie Sanders compared to the large rally
version of him in 2016.
Ali Vitali.
- And selfies.
(laughs)
- Right? Unbelievable.
Ali, you have been
covering Elizabeth Warren.
She also seems to be having
something of a moment.
What's the sense in her campaign about
where her support is coming from,
is it coming from Bernie's supporters,
is it coming from elsewhere,
and how do they make
sure that they continue
that slow, steady build that
they've been working on?
- Well you say slow and steady
and that really has been
the mantra over here.
When you talk to folks on the campaign,
they've really long-held this theory
that the polls will rise and fall,
but that to them the ultimate
thing that you can't get back
in a campaign is time.
That's why Elizabeth Warren
was one of the earliest people
in this race to launch her campaign.
She's been getting
folks out on the ground.
I know we haven't seen her
quarter two numbers yet,
but last quarter we saw that
her burn rate was so high
because they're investing
so heavily in ground game.
And in a place like Nevada
where we were last night
and where she's gonna be in Reno tonight,
she's really seeing some of that pay off,
potentially at the
expense of Bernie Sanders
because as Shaq and I have
seeing over the course
of the past several months,
voters who like her on policy
recognize that there might be
a policy twin in Bernie Sanders,
but they're not buying him
as the messenger necessarily.
Listen to what one voter
told me last night.
- Bernie is not on my
list this time around,
I think we all heard his plans last time
and it didn't get him the nomination.
I think we're ready for someone new.
And when I watch the debates,
Bernie to me personally he
came across as kind of angry
and in your face and that's
not what we need right now.
I'm done with in your face.
- This is the reality of the new
landscape for Bernie Sanders.
Last time around,
it was him versus Hillary Clinton.
This time around,
it's him and his ideas
as the central focus,
but maybe a lot of other
messengers who can pick up
where Bernie Sanders left off, Kasie.
- Yeah, that's a good point.
Interesting, interesting
comments from that voter
that you found there, Ali.
Ginger Gibson, the
Sanders campaign insists
that they're gonna try to,
they're gonna keep their base,
they're gonna try to reach
out to disillusioned voters,
perhaps even people who voted for Trump
to try to get ahead in this primary,
but the reality is,
he seems to be basically, if not falling,
then right where he was and
in a crowded field like this,
that's a tough spot to be.
- I think the biggest
debate inside Washington
when it comes to Bernie Sanders right now
is where is his floor.
People have suggested that
he might already be there,
that this is his strident
supporters backing him
and he hasn't grown beyond that,
that he's really sort of
capped out at that bottom level
but he hasn't appeared to
evolve or to grow his base
in a way that would bring more people in,
particularly when there are more people
on the stage with him
of which to choose from.
The party has changed a
lot in the last four years.
The voters have changed a
lot in the last four years,
and largely Bernie Sanders
has stayed the same.
And they will tell you,
oh he's got new proposals,
he's evolved, he's changed so much,
but really, the Bernie Sanders
we saw on that 2016 stage
is the same Bernie
Sanders we saw last week.
- [Kasie] Right, and he was
hesitant then to talk about,
he'll talk about economic
justice but he won't necessarily
talk about social justice
through a racial lens,
which of course is what
a lot of these voters
are looking for this time around.
Ginger Gibson, Shaq Brewster, Ali Vitali,
thank you guys very much.
The stage is set and the
tanks have taken to the mall.
But concern over the
President's Fourth of July
salute to America is
only growing across D.C.
The reasons why, coming up next.
(slow techno music)
- Everyone wants to feel
confident when hiring pros
for their home projects.
And at Angie's List,
we have what you need to
make the right choice.
Find specialized pros in your area
for any kind of home project.
Check their ratings,
read verified reviews from your neighbors.
Then easily request
quotes from multiple pros
with just a few clicks.
Find all the pros you need to know,
all for free.
Go to AngiesList.com today.
- [Shaq] Pain thinks it makes the rules.
But the rules just changed.
New IcyHot Lidocaine Dry Spray.
Instant dry technology.
No mess, no residue, fast-acting relief.
Rise from pain.
New IcyHot Lidocaine Dry Spray.
- I switched to MiraLAX
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives forcefully stimulate
the nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX works with the water in your body
to unblock your system naturally.
And it doesn't cause bloating, cramping,
gas, or sudden urgency.
MiraLAX. Look for the pink cap.
- As a real estate agent,
I've learned it's excess
moisture that causes musty odors.
Pro tip, use DampRid.
- [Announcer] New DampRid drop-in tabs
attract and trap excess
moisture out of the air,
eliminating musty odors.
- Works every time.
- [Announcer] Get rid of dampness.
♪ DampRid. ♪
(low techno music)
- [Announcer] Everybody
has a visor in their car,
but a visor in the
wrong place can actually
make it harder to see.
- Nick Bolton here with the
latest from Bell and Howell.
We call it Tac Visor.
- [Announcer] Inspired by the face shields
used by our American fighter pilots.
- Tac Visor can do things
no ordinary visor can do.
Like block blinding glare
without blocking your view.
So invisible dangers
suddenly become visible,
and enhanced colors to give you vision
as sharp as an eagle's.
The secret is Bell and Howell's
light-filtering technology.
Nothing to see, right?
But look again as we
hold up our Tac Visor.
Our colorful American eagle is revealed.
Amazing.
- Think it's a trick?
Bring it in, guys.
Well check out what happens
when I show it to these people.
Hop in, take a look at that windshield,
tell me what you see.
- A blank screen.
- Just a blank screen.
- Nothing, blank.
- Go ahead pull down that Tac
Visor and take a look again.
- Whoa! What the.
- That is amazing!
- That's crazy1!
- How does it do that?
- Best of all, Tac Visor is
easy to install in any car.
- [Announcer] Simply slide to adjust,
and in just seconds.
- Ready to rock and roll.
- [Announcer] So, if you
need to block blinding glare
without blocking your view,
then you need a Bell and Howell Tac Visor.
- There's just nothing like
it on the market today.
- [Announcer] Act now and get
a Tac Visor for just $19.99.
And we'll even ship it to you free.
Only a Tac Visor features
Bell and Howell's precision
and quality and is backed
by our lifetime guarantee.
But wait, order today
and we'll upgrade you
to our two-in-one Tac Visor.
Just pay a separate fee.
When the sun goes down,
use the night vision visor
to improve visibility
and block dangerous glare
from oncoming headlights.
This offer won't last long,
so don't delay.
Here's how to get yours today.
- [Narrator] To order, call 1-800-965-2841
or go to tacvisor.com.
That's 1-800-965-2841 or
order online at tacvisor.com.
That's 1-800-965-2841.
- People say, if you have
occasional constipation,
you should know the location
of a decent bathroom.
My gut says take new
Benefiber Healthy Balance.
This daily supplement helps maintain
digestive health naturally
while relieving occasional
constipation and abdominal discomfort.
New Benefiber Healthy Balance.
(soft techno music)
- Tomorrow's the big day.
President Trump's controversial
salute to America.
Some Bradley fighting
vehicles which were spotted
heading towards the mall,
but they are not the
only things on the move.
According to The Washington Post,
the National Park Service is
diverting nearly $2.5 million
in entrance and recreation fees
that were primarily intended
to improve parks across the country.
Just a fraction of the
extra costs the government
faces as a result of this event.
President promising a show of a lifetime,
defended his production
on Twitter saying quote,
"The cost of our great
Salute to America tomorrow
will be very little compared
to what it is worth.
We own the planes, we have the pilots,
the airport is right next door,
all we need is the fuel.
We own the tanks and all.
Fireworks are donated by
two of the greats. Nice!"
Joining me now from the
national mall in Washington,
NBC's Monica Alba and NBC's
Courtney Kube joins me
also from the Pentagon.
Monica, let me start with you.
You are watching all of this unfold.
We've seen some reports of
tourists not able to get
into the Lincoln Memorial,
and I think clearly one
of the big differences
here from years past is that
suddenly there is a VIP section
for the best seats in the house that,
it used to be whoever,
the egalitarian ruled the day,
first come first served.
- That's right, Kasie, exactly.
And as you can see over my
shoulder those preps continue.
And we're actually gonna
be able to show you exactly
where President Trump is gonna be speaking
from tomorrow evening.
And as you can see,
the customary bullet-proof glass
that surrounds the President
at such a large-scale public event.
But to your point about the tickets,
this is open and free to the public,
but certainly those who
have access to tickets
from the Republican National Committee,
and even the Trump Campaign
are actually gonna have
some of the best seats in the house.
Those folks are gonna
be kind of in a primary
section in the front and they'll actually
have a very good view it seems,
of some of those military
vehicles that you mentioned.
So, right now we can actually see there
is a Bradley fighting
vehicle which was parked
over on 23rd and Independence,
and moved here just a short time ago.
Just a small fraction
of the military might
that will be on full display tomorrow.
And of course that's
what the President wants.
He wants these optics and he
wants to show this to the world
and he was inspired actually
first two summers ago
when he was in Paris with
President Emmanuel Macron
at that military parade and said,
"Hey I would really like
to do this in Washington."
So, originally, the idea
was gonna be to do that
over a Veteran's Day holiday,
but of course that got scrapped
because the price tag was so high.
So that's one of the
big questions here too,
we don't know how much it's gonna cost,
there are a lot of elements here,
there are gonna be military fly overs,
there will be all the
military branches represented.
And then of course the big question,
will this turn more campaign rally
than a typically non-partisan event?
That all remains to be seen,
but we can see as the preps get under way,
and they're doing some sound checks here,
they are getting ready and
yes security has been tight.
There aren't tourists allowed
inside the Lincoln Memorial
anymore and they probably won't
be allowed until this event
is all over tomorrow.
This taking center stage here
on the National Mall, Kasie.
- Courtney Kube, to pick up on that point
Monica was making about
the risk of it turning
it into a campaign rally,
I mean first of all,
how unusual is this for
the United States military
to be involved in a production like this?
How much historically is this something
that they are used to doing
and second of all,
what is the level of concern
around the possibility
of politics to play into an event that,
I mean obviously we know
our military leaders
are typically supposed
to steer clear of that.
- So, of course the military
is not allowed to be involved
officially in any kind of political event.
There are very specific rules
and candidly in the last year or two,
we've seen more and more
guidelines and memos
just in the past several weeks than acting
Secretary of Defense Patrick
Shanahan put out a memo
with guidelines reminding people
that the military is apolitical.
Fourth of July is typically
not a military holiday.
It's not like Veteran's Day
where you see military leaders
and bands and whatnot spread
throughout the country
and involved in these kinds of activities.
Since this parade,
the first of the planning,
when we first heard
mention of this parade,
there has been concern
from U.S. military leaders
here in the Pentagon and around,
that this could turn into
some sort of a political rally
that would become awkward
for both the military leaders
who are there and the
military who are involved.
Defense officials who we
have spoken with this week
say that they are assured
that President Trump,
his speech will be less than 20 minutes,
he will speak for about four
minutes about each service.
There's some belief that
he wants the joint chiefs,
for the most part it will
be the vice chairman,
I'm sorry, the vice
chiefs who will be there,
that he wants each
individual representative
at some point to come
up and stand with him,
when they're reviewing their aircraft,
when he's talking about them or whatever,
but there is some concern that in fact
that could look like some
sort of a political statement
or a political rally.
But what's important to note here
is that the Pentagon lawyers
they went through this event
as they do when there's
any military participation
in an event,
and they found that in fact it is legal
and they are allowed to both participate
and attend this event, Kasie.
- And so has the Pentagon
reviewed the President's remarks,
do they know what he's gonna say,
to make sure that they are
comfortable having their guys
stand up next to him?
- At this point,
not that they are aware of
that they've reviewed him.
All they've been given is this
guidance that he wills speak
about the various services here.
So, at this point assuming
the weather holds out
and they have these fly overs,
each of the military
services will be represented
with this air show.
You mentioned there's gonna be
the F-22's, F-35's, the Blue Angels,
they will all culminate
with the Navy's Blue Angels,
who of course,
they participate in any
number of recruiting events
all over the country,
all over the world.
So that won't be uncommon.
But what we don't quite
know yet is exactly,
will the President stick
to the script here,
or will he go off on a
political tangent, Kasie?
- Always the question,
Monica Abla, Courtney Kube,
thank you guys both, very much.
Today, the country said
farewell to a hero.
One more thing, up next.
(soft drum music)
- [Announcer] Sandals has
won the world's best 23 years
in a row by redefining excellence,
and by including the best of everything.
Sandals, the world's only five
star luxury included resort.
Call 1-800-sandals.
- [Shaq] Pain thinks it makes the rules.
But the rules just changed.
New IcyHot Lidocaine Dry Spray.
Instant dry technology.
No mess, no residue, fast-acting relief.
Rise from pain.
- If something happened to you,
what would happen to them?
Their home, their education, their future?
You need life insurance.
And chances are, SelectQuote
can help you get it
for less than a dollar a day.
- [Announcer] SelectQuote
found Jacob 40 a $500,000
policy for only $19 a month.
And SelectQuote found
his wife Wendy a $500,000
for only $17 a month.
- Our secret?
At SelectQuote, we
aggressively comparison shop
up to 10 highly-rated
companies to find you
the company with the best rates.
- [Announcer] We found
Gary 35 a $1,000,000 policy
for only $22 a month.
- Why pay more?
Give your family the security they need
at a price you can afford.
- [Announcer] Call 1-800-289-6042,
or go to selectquote.com now
and get the insurance your family needs.
- [Man] At a price you can afford.
SelectQuote. We shop. You Save.
- [Announcer] The app today.
(dramatic soft music)
- One more thing before we go.
Today, in New York, the
city and world said goodbye
to 9/11 first responder Luis Alvarez.
Chances are, you know the NYPD detective
from his final days spent on Capitol Hill
fighting for law makers
to continue funding
for the 9/11 compensation fund.
But Alvarez became an American
hero long before then.
Atop the rubble of ground zero,
spending months combing
for survivors and remains.
Many of them his fellow fallen comrades,
despite having trouble breathing,
Detective Alvarez kept going,
like many others did,
after the EPA told them the air
at ground zero was just fine.
But it wasn't.
Three years ago,
Alvarez began his fight
against colon cancer.
Despite growing weak from
round after round of chemo,
he never stopped fighting.
- You made me come down here the day
before my 69th round of chemo.
And I'm gonna make sure
that you never forget
to take care of the 9/11 responders.
If I can help just one
more first responder,
then it makes it all worthwhile for me.
Really, it sounds like a cliche,
but it's the truth.
- [Kasie] Sadly, Alvarez never made it
to that 69th round of chemo,
instead going into hospice shortly
after he returned from Capitol Hill.
He passed away this weekend,
joining more than 2,000
first responders to pass away
from illnesses related to
their work at ground zero.
At today's ceremony,
in the same church he grew up attending
after moving from Cuba
at just one year old,
his priest relayed the single request
that Luis had for his funeral:
that we all remember
the brave men and women
who went before him and
those who continue to fight
now that he's gone.
Today, as the 53 year old was remembered,
the last words he's known to
have said were recited quote,
"At the end, the only thing that matters
is how much we loved."
May he rest in peace.
That wraps things up for this hour.
I'm Kasie Hunt in Washington.
Please do follow me on Twitter
and catch me every
Sunday night on Kasie DC.
Ali Velshi picks things up
from New York right now.
- Kasie thank you,
have yourself a great
rest of the afternoon
and a happy Fourth of July.