- [Presenter] Read verified reviews
and easily request multiple quotes.
Find all the pros you need
to know at angielist.com.
- Hi.
- [Woman] Look at how great you look.
- Thank you.
- I've been on a diet for
as long as I can remember.
- I even cut out bread
and pasta for a day.
- I decided something needed
to change and then I tried Noom.
- Noom worked for me.
- It's an easy to stick to program
that actually changed my habits.
- They say it's based on a
cognitive behavioral approach.
I just say it works.
- It just clicked, it works.
It worked with Noom.
- [Presenter] Visit noom.com
and lose the weight for good.
- [Man] I can't tell you
who I am or what I witnessed
but I can tell you Liberty Mutual
customized my car insurance so
I only pay for what I needed.
(camera clicks)
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
(water splashes)
- [Presenter] Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty, Liberty, Liberty ♪
- [Presenter] If you live with diabetes
why finger stick when you can scan?
With the FreeStyle Libre
14 day system just scan
the sensor with your reader, iPhone,
or Android and manage your diabetes.
With a FreeStyle Libre 14 day system,
a continuous glucose monitor,
you can check your glucose levels
any time without finger sticks.
Ask your doctor to write a prescription
for the FreeStyle Libre 14 day system.
You can do it without finger sticks.
Learn more out freestylelibre.us.
- If you bought a
timeshare for your family
by now you've learned the ugly truth.
Timeshares are the only
thing that you can buy
that you don't know how
much it's gonna cost
or when it's gonna end.
It's like giving them a blank check
for annual maintenance
and assessment fees.
Sounds crazy, right?
The ugly truth is that this never ends.
Even when you die your family
will be stuck with this burden.
Hello, I'm Church
McDowell and 10 years ago
I founded Wesley Financial
Group with one goal in mind:
helping good folks just like you
cancel their timeshare contract.
And what that means for
you and your family:
no more mortgage payments,
no more maintenance fee
surprises, and no more timeshare.
So call today.
The call is free, the
information kit is free,
and I guarantee if we can't cancel
your timeshare contract
you'll pay nothing.
- [Presenter] You can legally
get out of your timeshare.
For your free information
kit explaining how
call 800-395-8811, 500-395-8811.
- [Presenter] The app today.
- How do you learn how
to run when you've never
done anything remotely like this before?
- We're prepare to do it in a
novel way, in an original way
and we wanna make sure we're
writing our own playbook.
- Do you think we should
keep troops in Afghanistan?
- I do not and I believe that we need
to it though in a responsible way.
(engaging music)
- Where do you see your party right now?
- It's going to be how do we
think government should work
and who do we think
government should work for.
(engaging music)
(patriotic music)
- It was July 2017, when
Donald Trump, just months
into his presidency visited
France on Bastille Day.
He attended a military parade
at Emmanuel Macron's side.
He was impressed.
The military might, the
soldiers, the tanks,
he wanted his own parade.
Two years later it looks
like he is getting his wish.
Here in Washington, the Lincoln
Memorial is being prepped
for a Trump-branded July
4th spectacular, including:
a speech, a possible
Air Force One flyover,
and you guessed it, tanks.
There's not only concern
about the potential
partisan nature of the President's event
but those tanks have
also proven a bit tricky
for the Commander in Chief.
Here he was yesterday.
- We're gonna have some
tanks stationed outside.
You gotta be pretty careful
with the tanks because
the roads have a tendency
not to like to carry
heavy tanks, so we have to
put 'em in certain areas.
But we have the brand new Sherman tanks
and we have the brand new Abram tanks,
and we have some incredible
equipment, military equipment
on display, brand-new and
we're very proud of it.
- So a couple issues
here for the President.
One, Sherman tanks have not been
in active service since the 1950s.
Problem two, the tanks that are coming
weigh about 60 tons each and
there is very real concern
that they could do major damage
to the capital city's streets, bridges,
and of course our country's
famed National Mall.
Joining me now, Washington Post
Senior Affairs correspondent
Juliet Eilperin, and former
Senior Advisor to Ash Carter
and Professor at Amherst
College, Mark Jacobson.
- Juliet, we're gonna talk with Mark here
in a second about the tanks, but first
the concerns potentially
here about partisanship
on what is typically a patriotic holiday
celebrated by all
Americans, Kellyanne Conway
this morning insisted that
it would be apolitical.
Take a look.
- This is a public event,
it's open to the public.
The public is welcome
to come and celebrate
our great country, the greatest democracy,
the Constitution, all the amendments,
not just the 1st Amendment that
seems to interest you only,
the 2nd Amendment, all
the other, but really just
the birth of this country,
the greatest democracy that ever lived.
I'm not gonna allow you to politicize it.
- Fair to say that it
is open to the public
however there is the VIP
section right up front
where typically anyone would be able to be
in that area of the Mall
to watch the fireworks
if you got there early enough.
But now the RNC has
gotten tickets and the DNC
tells our Peter Alexander
that they haven't received
an allotment of tickets
for that area at all.
It kind of undermines this argument.
- Sure, the fact that
there's limited VIP seating,
which we reported on last week, shows you
that really that there are
some political elements.
Now the RNC, we checked with them today,
they're arguing that in the same way
that if a Democrat was in the White House
they would give tickets to their party.
That these things happen for
White House holiday tours,
for things like that, that's
accurate although again
those are where you have
limits on who can be here.
This traditionally has
been an entirely open event
and its now being modified to have
limited access in part of the Mall.
- [Kasie] And we are of
course gonna get a speech
from the President, I
mean it's hard to argue
that any speech in this kind
of a forum would be an apolitical one.
- Well one of the things is it really
will matter what he
says, whether he refers
to for example any of the Democrats
who are currently running
for president in 2020,
whether he talks about
polling, those are all comments
that could trigger this provision where
under federal appropriations law
you can't use public resources
for political purposes
and if they deem that part of
this is a political speech,
the campaign, Trump's
presidential re-election campaign
might have to reimburse the U.S. Treasury
for some of the expenses of this event.
- So speaking of those
expenses, Mark Jacobson,
these tanks are logistically
difficult to get here.
This is also gonna cost the US military
not an insignificant amount of money.
We're not exactly sure how much,
but does the military
community kind of agree here
with the President that
this is a good idea?
- I suspect the military
community and going based
on conversations I've had
with those on active duty
and veterans, there's
a a mixed view on this.
One, if you look at this entire week,
this should just be blip compared
to all the mistakes Trump seems
to have made on the
national security front,
but at the same time you
a National Park Service
that's in debt already, well there's
a cost that they can't bear.
You have a bunch of troops
who thought they we're gonna
spend July 4th with their families
who are no longer going to spend July 4th
with their families
and as suggested before
this is exactly the opposite of what
the founding fathers meant
in terms of symbolism.
I mean the United States
was born of a fear
of a standing army, the
4th of July has never been
a military celebration; it's a celebration
of political independence and the ideals
of the enlightenment in this
traditionally American way.
It's not supposed to look like North Korea
or the Soviet Union and that's
what Trump's set up here.
- That's a great point
about our founding fathers
and the way they envisioned this holiday
and what freedom at the time
from England actually meant--
- If I could, there's a
great Erma Baumbach quote,
where the late humorist
she talks about 4th of July
is about potato salad and
hot dogs and isn't it great
that we live in a country
where we don't have
to have a parade with guns,
and troops, and tanks,
and that that the true
patriotism on this day
is feeling like you've eaten too much.
And that's freedom.
- John McCain, there's a
non-profit organization
that's gonna print out shirts
that feature the USS John McCain.
What's your take on the symbolism of that?
Is seems as though the
White House certainly wants
to make sure that the people right
in front of the President
are supporting him.
- As you will recall there
was this mission accomplished
moment during the visit to
Japan, where the USS John McCain
was supposedly gonna have its name hidden
and its sailors weren't invited
to the presidential address.
I think that's again is a way of poking
back at the President.
Again, it's a day where
we celebrate our freedoms
including freedom of speech,
freedom of expression.
I think again the White House should
just have Trump go golfing.
That's what presidents
actually do on July 4th.
They go golf.
This would be a great day to
do it, not to get involved,
sit in the White House which used to have
a great view of the fireworks,
and leave this a celebration
of the American people
by the American people.
- All right Juliet
Eilperin, Mark Jacobson,
thank you guys both very much
for your perspectives and reporting today.
Coming up next, Hispanic
Caucus Chair Joaquin Castro
joins me to talk about what he witnessed
during a tour yesterday of
a Texas border facility.
Here's what he said just
moments after that tour.
- One of the women said that she was told
by an agent to drink
water out of the toilet.
These are the conditions that have been
created by the Trump administration.
These are the inhumane
conditions that folks are facing.
- In America every car is a
declaration of independence
and to celebrate our nation's birthday
we'll do it at Daytona.
(patriotic music)
In a 200 mile per hour blur
of red, white, and blue.
- [Presenter] Thanks, Golden Corral.
Dan get his slow, smoked sirloin
and my little trio are as happy as shrimp.
Oops clams, and mom got it
all hook, line and sirloin.
The slowest smoked
sirloin and shrimp trio.
Golden Corral, the only one for everyone.
- As a real estate agent I've learned
it's excess moisture
that causes musty odor.
Pro tip, use DampRid.
- [Presenter] New DampRid
drop in tabs attract
and trap excess moisture out of the air,
eliminating musty odors.
- Works every time.
- [Presenter] Get rid of dampness.
♪ DampRid ♪
- [Presenter] Let's get down to business,
the business of family time and down time,
and you time, and forgetting
what time it is altogether.
Modernized Comfort Inns and
Suites have been refreshed
because when your business is making
time, our business is you.
Get the lowest price
guaranteed on all Choice Hotels
when you book direct at choicehotels.com.
♪ Imagine me and you and you
and me so happy together ♪
♪ I can't see me loving nobody ♪
♪ But you for all my life ♪
- Here you go little guy.
A cockroach can survive submerged
underwater for 30 minutes.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
(dramatic music)
Not getting in today.
- [Presenter] Terminix, defenders of home.
- You know that expensive
watch you always wanted?
It only costs a fraction
of the price to make.
- We thought that was crazy.
So we made our own watch company.
(engaging music)
- We created unique watch designs
launched online at fair
prices, developed new styles,
shipped to over 160
countries around the world,
and created a community, now you don't
have to overpay for a nice watch.
- Instead join the movement.
Shop now at mvmt.com
(engaging music)
- [Presenter] Take Prilosec OTC
and take control of heartburn.
So you don't have to stash antacids here,
here, or here, kick your antacid habit
with Prilosec OTC, one pill a day,
24 hours, zero heartburn.
- Pain thinks it makes the rules.
But the rules just changed.
New Icy Hot lidocaine dry spray.
Instant dry technology, no mess,
no residue, fast-acting relief.
Rise from pain.
♪ Limu Emu ♪
- [Presenter] And Doug.
- What do all these people
have in common Limu?
Exactly, nothing.
They're completely different people.
That's why they need
customized car insurance
from Liberty Mutual; they'll
only pay for what they need.
(change clanks)
Yes and they could save a ton.
We've done it again Limu.
(emu squawks)
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, liberty, liberty, liberty ♪
- [Presenter] Mesothelioma,
it's all we do.
With nine offices across the country
we are large enough to
take on big corporations.
Let us come meet with you.
Call us at 1-800-500-1895,
that's 1-800-500-1895.
- At Timeshare Exit Team we've helped
thousands of people get out
of their timeshares forever.
- Timeshare Exit Team sent us a letter
saying that we were free
and clear of the timeshare.
So that was a time to celebrate.
- If you're unhappy with your timeshare
we would love to help you find a way out.
- [Presenter] Call 1-800-837-3110.
- [Presenter] A free case review.
(engaging music)
- At this hour, nationwide
demonstrations are underway
with protestors demanding
the closures of detention
facilities holding migrant
children and families.
Advocacy groups organized
more than 150 demonstrations.
Some outside of congressional
district offices.
While others gathered outside
of detention facilities.
The protests follow
reports of poor conditions
inside some migrant detention
facilities in Texas.
And visits to those facilities
by Democratic members
of the Congressional Hispanic
Caucus just yesterday.
This, as customs and border
protection has launched
an investigation following
a ProPublica report
exposing a secret
Facebook group of current
and former border patrol;
in it members reportedly
mocked the death of migrants
and posted sexist memes.
We should note that NBC
News has not verified
the Facebook group or seen the posts.
Joining me now, MSNBC
correspondent Gabe Gutierrez.
Gabe, you're in El Paso
I understand speaking
with pediatricians that have
treated migrant children
released from custody; what are they
telling you about how
these kids are doing?
- Hi there Kasie, well we're
outside of Annunciation House
and we've been coming to this
shelter for the past year
or so since the family
separation crisis of last year
and they deal with a lot of migrants.
They take in a lot of migrants
that have been processed
by CBP and by ICE and they
end up at this shelter
before they're sent away
all across the country
as they await their asylum proceedings
and what we're hearing now
is over the last couple
of weeks they've gone from
taking about 1000 migrants
a day, now it's about 100, 150.
But we're also speaking with
some of the pediatricians
that are treating some of these children
including Dr. Lisa Ayoub-Rodriquez.
YOu're a local pediatrician
at a local hospital
and you are treating
some of these children,
very young children, while
they're in CBP custody
if they're hospitalized
and then after, correct?
So tell me what are you seeing?
- That's right, for
the last several months
we've had the privilege
to be able to take care
of children who while are in CBP custody
if they need to be hospitalized,
they go to the hospital
and we care for them,
or if after they are
discharged from CPB custody
and they're in Annunciation
House, if they need
to be admitted to the
hospital we take care
of them there as well.
We see a lot of common childhood illnesses
in this population, a lot of influenza,
stomach bugs, those kinds of things.
The population is really
unique in that they get
a little bit sicker
because they already are
a little compromised in
that they're dehydrated,
their nutrition isn't as expected,
so they have the potential
to be sicker, faster.
- When we toured the Clint,
Texas border patrol station
last week we weren't allowed
to talk to these children.
Members of Congress have now been there
and they are telling stories of their
communication with these children.
What have you heard some of these parents,
some of these children, have you
heard anything that troubles you?
- Yeah, I often talk to the families
who have been in CPB custody and ask them
a little bit about what their
time there has been like.
Most recently a met a young
mom who had a newborn baby
and who was talking about
the challenges of keeping
her little newborn warm;
so they had given her
a plastic blanket and
the baby was in a onesie,
but really she was snuggling with the baby
and she was like, I just
couldn't keep the baby warm,
just despite whatever I
did I just couldn't keep
my baby warm, she talked
about the little hands
and the feet being blue
which was troubling to me and
that's just a simple, basic
human need that concerned me.
- Thank you Dr. Ayoub-Rodriguez
and one last question:
based on your experience and
your opinion should children
this young be kept in these
types of holding facilities?
- No children should be
in a holding facility.
They need access to their basic needs.
If their child is sick they
need access to medical care
by a trained pediatric professional.
Really it's not a place for any kid to be.
- Dr. thank you for speaking with us.
So Kasie, this, the
ongoing situation down here
on the border, earlier we were
at that border patrol station
in Clint, Texas, of course as
you mentioned that controversy
following the ProPublica report.
This appears to be a debate
with no end in sight.
Kasie.
- Absolutely heartbreaking to
hear about an infant so cold
that their hands and feet turn blue.
Gabe Gutierrez, thank you very much
as always for your reporting on this.
When the delegation of
Democratic lawmakers toured
those migrant detention
centers along the border
they were told to surrender
their devices before
they would be allowed
to enter the facilities.
But Congressman Joaquin
Castro of Texas was able
to sneak a phone, in with
the consent of the women
in custody Castro filmed their small cell
which included a toilet
but no running water.
He posted the images on
Twitter saying quote:
many said they had not bathed for 15 days.
Some had been separated from children.
Some had been held for more than 50 days.
Several complained that they
had not received their medication.
Joining me now, Texas Democratic
Congressman Joaquin Castro.
Congressman Castro is the Chairman
of the Congressional Hispanic Caucus.
Congressman thank you
for being here today.
- Yeah, thanks for having me.
- So I wanna start with the basics here.
I think it's hard for a
lot of Americans to wrap
their heads around the
idea that you as members
of Congress, regardless of
what party you may belong to
aren't able to go into
facilities that our government
is paying for and actually
document what you see.
What did it take for you to get your phone
into this facility so that those
images could get out there?
- I just kept in my pocket when
they told us to put it on the table.
We asked them repeatedly,
we challenged them
and asked them what law allows them
to force us to keep our phones and cameras
away from the facility and
the border patrol chief there
couldn't give us an answer, in
fact there was a lawyer there
and she couldn't give us an answer,
and so at that point
as far as I'm concerned
they have no right to
try to keep legislators
who are entrusted with
oversight of their agency
from documenting what they see.
Particularly, given what's at stake
and given what's going on right now.
- So what in your view could
possibly be the explanation?
I think it strikes a lot
of people that they simply
don't want anyone to find out
what is actually going on.
- And I think that that's right.
I think that they're scared.
I think that the reason
things don't change the way
they should is because these
things are kept secret.
For example, there was
a point at which we were
in one of tents that was empty.
They had already moved
everybody out and these are dark
tents with chain-link fences
and when the search happened
they had maybe 100, 200 people
in there and they had said
you can't take pictures because you can't
violate the privacy of these children.
And so we said okay
well this tent is empty.
There's nobody in here.
Can we take a photo of the tent?
And they said no, you can't
take a photo of the tent.
It doesn't make any sense.
They're trying to keep everything secret.
- So they are of course pushing
back on some of the claims
that you've heard from
these women that you show
in your video and from
others that you spoke to.
Do you have any reason not to believe
what these migrant detainees told you?
- I don't, they spoke sincerely.
In fact, there was a point
where one of the women
who was Cuban, she spoke
some English and in front
of all of us, many of
the legislators and also
several CBP officers, she
challenged them very directly
and said that they were
not telling the truth
about the standard of
care and the treatment,
and she said that some
of the agents had used
derogatory words, language,
against the women.
Now, I'm not saying that she said that all
of the agents did that, but she said that,
it sounded to me like a few of them had.
So she very directly
challenged them in front
of all us and that's one of the reasons
that these women were
scared of retribution.
But, if there's a dispute
about what the truth is
in those facilities then I think
there's a very easy way to solve that.
They have cameras up
in all of those rooms.
They can simply put out the
video from all those cameras
and they can let the press do their jobs
and go inside there, and the press
can be the tiebreaker
about what's going on.
- So the government has footage
of what's gone on in these facilities?
They've been videotaping,
all of this is on camera
and yet we as the American
public just can't see it?
- Yeah look, they knew that I was
taking a picture of those folks.
They knew that I pulled my camera out.
I'm sure somebody was
watching me in that room.
I saw the overhead camera right there.
There were probably five agents
that we're watching that.
So they have footage of all of that.
- So to pick up on another
point that you were making.
You said in this facility
there were border patrol agents
or personnel that have
been accused of behaving
frankly in way that's not becoming
of people who wear a uniform
of the United States.
There's also been ProPublica
reporting on a secret
Facebook group that many
border patrol agents
and former agents are a
member of where they have said
some pretty despicable things
allegedly and that there
is now an investigation going on.
What should happen to
the people who are found
to be making these kinds of comments
and be treating people this way?
- Well the people that made
those very direct comments
about some of the members of Congress,
about some of the people that
were entrusted in their care,
they are desensitized to
the point of being dangerous
to the migrants and
also to their coworkers
and they need to be relieved of duty.
They really should not
be wearing any uniform
that represents the
United States of America.
And also the agents that
were on there that did not
turn those people in need to be dealt with
and held accountable in some way also.
- Do you take any issue with
how your Democratic leaders
in Congress handled
the recent funding bill
to try and help alleviate this crisis?
I mean the money that
ultimately is gonna be spent
as part of that bill doesn't
have some of the restrictions
that Democrats wanted, many progressives
were very angry about
how that all played out.
Do you feel as though your
leadership acted in bad faith
and did Congress give too much
to the Trump administration
as they claim that they're
trying to deal with this?
- Well I think they mostly
ran up against a buzzsaw,
Mitch McConnell and President
Trump who don't care very much
for the people that are in
those detention centers.
There's no question that we
needed stronger safeguards
or guardrails around that
money so that it can't be
transferred out and away
from humanitarian aid,
and also, we also needed not just to pump
a bunch more cash into these facilities,
for example, when we passed
through some of the walkways
we saw stacks of granola bars.
I looked in another cell
and there was a family
that was eating ramen, they were huddled
on the floor eating ramen noodles.
So it's not just about more cash for them
to buy ramen noodles and granola bars.
You have to change the medical standards
and also the standards
of care and treatment,
and unfortunately in that
Senate bill that finally passed
there isn't enough of that;
we need to do a better job.
- All right, Texas
congressman Joaquin Castro
thank you very much for
your time today, sir.
I appreciate it.
- Thank you.
- Coming up next the President's
quest to not be forgotten.
(engaging music)
- [Presenter] Parents have a
way of imagining the worst.
Especially when your easily
distracted teenager has the car.
(somber music)
At Subaru we're taking
on distracted driving
with sensors that alert you
when your eyes are off the road.
(brakes screech)
The all new Subaru Forester.
The safest Forester ever.
(engaging music)
- [Presenter] Your brain
changes as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain with
an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish.
In clinical trials Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen, healthier brain, better life.
(stove simmers)
(rooster crows)
(engaging music)
- [Presenter] Introducing
the Blackstone griddle.
Outdoor cooking without the compromise.
Log on now to blackstoneproducts.com.
- [Presenter] Constipation
can happen all around us
you just need to know where to look.
Luckily there's Colace, it's number one,
doctor recommended stool softener brand
for occasional constipation.
- The dining room in my house
to me is the heart of our house.
When I found Article
there were so many times
that I picked up on something small
that was like oh, I
love that specific item.
- Article just spoke to me.
It had that look and feel, that design
that I really, really like.
- Whatever's in the chair
to make it comfortable.
It has a very durable feel to it.
I feel like this chair is going
to be part of our living
room for a very long time
- [Presenter] Shop beautiful, modern
furniture at article.com.
- [Presenter] Paul you're
the greatest neighbor.
You help us find the best
home improvement pros.
Get quotes and research
prices for our home projects.
- That, that's not me.
That's HomeAdvisor.
- [Presenter] You can't
expect your neighbors
to do it all so just ask HomeAdvisor.
(engaging music)
- [Presenter] Corey is living
with metastatic breast cancer
which is breast cancer that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking Ibrance
with an aromatase inhibitor
which is for postmenopausal woman
or for men with HR+, HER2-
metastatic breast cancer
as the first hormonal based therapy.
Ibrance plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease
progression versus letrozole.
Patients taking Ibrance can
develop low white blood cell
counts which may cause serious infections
that can lead to death;
before taking Ibrance
tell your doctor if
you have fever, chills,
or other signs of infection,
liver or kidney problems
are pregnant, breast-feeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects
include low red blood cell
and low platelet counts,
infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth, abnormalities
in liver blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash, and loss of appetite.
Corey calls it her new normal
because a lot has changed
but a lot hasn't; ask
your doctor about Ibrance,
the number one prescribed,
FDA approved, oral combination
treatment for HR+, HER2- MBC.
(engaging music)
- If there's one thing
that President Trump does
consistently it's provide
compliments usually, to himself.
As he was in a recent interview
with Fox News' Tucker Carlson.
- A lot of people gave me
a lot of credit for that.
- The public was on your side for sure.
- A lot of people said that was
a great presidential moment.
I won, they were totally
against me, I won.
I have millions and millions
of people on Twitter.
A poll just came out
today, I'm at 54 or 55
and they do say you can add
to whatever poll I have.
And yet I won and I'll win again.
- They do?
That interview was taped
during Trump's trip to Asia,
a trip that made history when he became
the first sitting president
to step into North Korea.
Whether that moment will
result in meaningful diplomacy
is still unclear but the President
already thinks that it did.
He told reporters that his presidency
was quote, the hottest show in town.
The New York Times Peter Baker wrote about
the President's quest for
superlatives, saying whatever
he is doing must be the first, the most,
the biggest and it
shapes his policy choices
even as he frames his own
narrative with the branding skills
of a career in business and entertainment.
And joining me now is New York Times
Chief White House correspondent
and MSNBC political analyst, Peter Baker.
Peter, I just saw your
tweet a couple minutes
before we came on the
air that in the course
of one news conference the
President used best nine times,
incredible 16 times, tremendous 28 times,
and great or greatest 50 times.
Kudos to whoever actually went through
and actually counted
up all of those words.
But the reality here is
sometimes he'll make statements
that are simply not
true in in the interest
of presenting himself in the
way that you write about.
- Yeah look, this is a salesman.
This is what his history
is, he's an entertainer
and I think he understands that repetition
and upselling in effect works,
and if facts are inconvenient
or get in the way you
just either ignore them
or rewrite them, and in this
case he has the best economy
ever, he's the strongest president ever,
the best negotiation
ever, the best deal ever,
and this has an impact,
it does in fact create
a narrative out there that
a lot of people appreciate,
and understand, and
agree with even if others
are spitting mad because he's playing
fast and loose with the facts.
He clearly wants to be
in the history books.
This is one of the reasons
why he goes to the DMZ
and he walks across that
line into North Korea
because he was told no other
president had done it before.
It's a first.
He likes to be somebody
who's done the first.
He likes to be someone
who's broken a barrier
and done something that
no one else has done.
The question, you just put it correctly,
is does this mean something more enduring?
And that's the unanswered question.
- In that interview with Tucker
Carlson, Peter, first of all
I people thought it was
interesting shall we say
that Carlson was on the trip acting
as a de facto foreign
policy advisor while his own
National Security Advisor
was off in Mongolia.
But setting that aside
there were some interesting,
interesting shall we say answers to some
of the question that Carlson posed.
I wanna show you his answer
on homelessness specifically
and then we'll talk about
it, let's take a look.
- In New York City, San
Francisco, Los Angeles
they've got a major problem with--
- It's very sad.
- [Carlson] With filth.
- Very sad.
- Why is that?
- It's a phenomemon that
started two years ago.
It's disgraceful.
I'm gonna maybe and I'm
looking at it very seriously.
I had a situation when
I first became president
where we had certain
areas of Washington D.C.
where that was starting to happen
and I ended it very quickly.
I said you can't do that.
When we have leaders of the world coming
into to see the President
of the United States
and they're riding down a
highway they can't be looking
at that, I really believe
that it hurts our country.
- So Peter, not only is he
saying in another example
of this phenomenon where
he solves all the problems
and does all of the
things, he says he removed
homeless people so that other
leaders wouldn't see them,
but he also says this is a phenomenon
that only started two years ago.
Where did that come from?
- Yeah, we've been trying
to figure that out today
as a matter of fact,
we've been scouring Fox
and some of the other places
he gets his information from
to see if he's reacting
to something specific
and it hard to understand
exactly, obviously
homelessness did not
just start two years ago.
There's no question that
there's been an uptick
in some places and in fact California
has been dealing with this.
I think it's been a big
issue in the last few weeks
in Los Angeles in particular.
But he sees not as a humanitarian
issue, the way he frames
it in that interview as well,
it's a public relations issue.
It's an issue you don't
world leaders to see
and therefore you wanna to get
these people out of the way,
not to make sure that they're
getting care or get them
into homes but to make sure
that they're not visible
for visiting leaders; that's a pretty
striking framework on his part.
But I don't know what he's talking about.
He says two years ago there was an issue
and he snaps his fingers
and suddenly it's gone.
I live in Washington,
lived here my whole life.
It's hard to know what he's talking about
because obviously homelessness
has been an issue here
for a long time, hasn't
changed specifically
in the last two years in a meaningful way.
- If anything it's gotten to be
one of more visible problems.
Peter Baker, thank you very much.
Also I would be remiss
if I didn't thank you
for that Western liberalism question
during the news conference;
we were all a little
taken aback by the
President's interpretation
of your question but thank
you for asking it sir
and thank you for being here today.
- Okay, thanks very much.
- As the field of Democratic
presidential candidates
prepare for the next
debate, climate change
remains a top issue among primary voters.
But how does a country
balance concerns over
the environment with the need for jobs
and revenue from industries like coal?
NBC's Cal Perry traveled
to Montana to find out.
Cal this is really the
central question as we try
to grapple with this as a country,
and as we frankly fail to
grapple with this as a country,
is there are a lot of people who depend
on these old industries
for their livelihoods
and making that transition
is incredibly difficult.
You talked to one
candidate who didn't make
the debate stage about all of this, right?
- Yeah, exactly right and
you're nailing the issue.
It's a difficult balance
especially in a place like Montana.
We went out there, we
spent time with governor,
Governor Bullock, he's trying to do that,
walk that fine line in an
industry and in a state
that still relies on fossil fuels.
Take a look.
(engaging music)
- I'm just absolutely amazed
at the big open skies.
- Everything that we're seeing around us
is just absolutely beautifully carved.
- One of the reasons I
wanted to come here was
just enjoy the park, but then tell people
that this place matters.
- These places are set aside
to be, because they're special.
These places are changing
and they're changing fast.
- It's gorgeous and you're
worried about the receding glaciers.
- While temperatures are
on the rise across America
Montana is warming twice as fast.
That according to the government's
own climate assessment.
The state is home to tiny coal towns
which historically have provided
the Western United States
with its energy needs,
small towns that are now
fighting for survival,
fighting in a state that also
has the nation's most
treasured natural wonders.
Anytime you're talking
about climate and politics
in America and Glacier National Park
has to be apart of that conversation.
According to the National Park Services
there were estimated 150
glaciers here in 1850.
Today, there's only 25.
Fewer days below freezing and more days
above 90 degrees is changing the state.
Less snowfall and earlier melt each year
means more fires, they're
bigger and burning longer.
Professor Diana Six studies
the impact of forest fires.
- This is naturally a fire landscape.
So it should be burning.
It's just that we're
seeing a lot of fires now.
- Dan Fagre measures the disappearing
glaciers for the U.S. Geological Survey.
Because of climate change his field
of study is naturally widening.
- When you have changes
like this they tend
to cascade through the whole system
and so the same things that
are melting the glaciers
are also causing changes
in forest fire frequency and severity.
- [Bullock] The current
administration says hell
they don't lose sleep about this.
I certainly do.
- [Cal] Montana governor
Steve Bullock is trying
to find a way to balance the realities
of climate change in a state with
an energy industry that depends on coal.
All the while doing it while running
for president inside the Democratic Party.
- As we make transitions we can't
be leaving communities behind.
There are folks, they've
worked their whole life
powering this country, and at times
Democrats and others try to
make them into the villains.
- For small towns like
Colstrip, Montana any discussion
of climate change is really gonna
be a discussion about revenue and jobs.
The plant behind me is within city limits.
Between that and the coal
mine officials here say
it accounts for 90% of the town's revenue.
Two buildings at Colstrip Power Plant
in operation since the mid-70s
will shut down just a
week after Christmas.
- They're gonna see a
drop in revenue locally.
- [Cal] Lori Shaw is a
former city council member.
She's also the founder of Colstrip United,
a pro-coal advocacy group.
- When a town, a state, a
community is wholly reliant
on only one or two industries
that makes us vulnerable
and I think we should always be looking
for ways to diversify and
become more resilient.
- Even while faced with
certain economic collapse
many here want people outside Montana
to know they understand
the difficult balance.
- We're not just like a bunch
of nature hating monsters.
We have our lives here
and we have families.
- I believe that we need to
have a beautiful environment
but what people don't get
is coal got us where we are.
- Climate change is real.
We might not be leaving anything
for our children or grandchildren
if we're not careful.
So we have to address it.
- We gotta address climate
change and we gotta do it now
and we actually are at
the point now as a country
where maybe it was lip
service 30 years ago,
but if were not taking
immediate and durable action now
the America that we're
gonna give and the world
that we're gonna give to
our kids and grandkids
isn't gonna be the America we live in.
(dramatic music)
- Kasie, the Trump administration
not only doesn't wanna
have this conversation,
they're actively trying
to prevent people from
having the conversation
including people that work
for the U.S. government.
For the Democrat's part,
the DNC has said they're not
gonna have a stand alone
debate on climate change.
However, as Rachel Maddow
would say, watch this space
because we understand they're
now re-discussing that
and there could be a vote in August.
So we may have some kind of
a climate change forum
on the horizon Kasie.
- It'll be interesting
to see if they do decide
that this something that deserves,
they received a lot of criticism I think
for saying, hey we can't spend
an entire evening talking
about this when of course
it's something that is just
gonna so dramatically affect all of us.
Cal Perry, thank you very
much for your reporting.
It looked like a fantastic,
beautiful trip to Montana.
Coming up next a tennis prodigy takes down
a tennis titan who happens to be her idol.
One More Thing, next.
(engaging music)
- [Presenter] It's only a matter of time
until your check engine light comes on
or worse yet your car needs repair.
That could mean a big
surprise auto repair bill.
Those repairs are more
expensive than ever.
A new engine can be over $5000.
A new transmission over $4000.
That's why it's so important
you call CarShield today.
CarShield is the number one auto
protection company in the country.
- I like CarShield because
they were reliable,
the were affordable, and
they were trustworthy.
- Well I think everybody
should have CarShield.
Once your manufacturer's
warranty is expired
there's just no big bills.
If we needed repairs,
CarShield was there for us.
- [Presenter] Now it's
your turn to get the peace
of mind that comes with having CarShield
so you can worry less about auto repairs.
Call or go online right now
to get CarShield for yourself.
Friendly, knowledgeable,
money-saving representatives
are available 24 hours a day.
So if your car is 20 years old or newer
just tell us the make and
model of your car or truck
to get an instant plan quote.
In a manner of minutes you can be covered.
- I was elated that I had CarShield.
I was more than happy.
- It's not fun when you
have a car and it's broken
and you can't pay for it get it fixed.
- [Presenter] Here's how
CarShield works: when your car
needs repair you take it
to your favorite mechanic
or even your dealer and CarShield
gets them paid directly.
That's why CarShield is America's
number one auto protection provider.
- CarShield is just the best thing
to take away the fear that
when something is going
to go wrong with you car, because it will
and CarShield is gonna
be there to back you up.
- My experience with CarShield
is that they absolutely
come through every time I need them.
- If my car breaks down I can count
on CarShield to cover it for me.
CarShield definitely has my back.
- [Presenter] Now it's the
time to make the smart choice
and protect yourself from
sky high auto repair bills.
Call now for a free and
instant protection plan quote.
It's only a matter of time
until repairs are needed
and once your car breaks
down it's too late.
Call 1-800-471-5552.
- [Presenter] This summer all eyes will be
on the US Women's National Team
in the FIFA Women's World Cup.
(engaging music)
Over 153 hours of
coverage, live from France.
The 2019 FIFA Women's World Cup
on Fox, FS1, and FS2.
Don't miss all 52 matches of
the FIFA Women's World Cup
live in stunning 4K on DIRECTTV.
If you don't have 4K ask for it today.
- [Man] Mr. Goodson.
- Not enough shelter for
us people on the street.
- Who is us?
- So now's probably not a great
time to get my library card.
- I am not prepared to be
in a standoff with a cop.
- [Man] Why do all this, for what?
- To let 'em know we still matter.
(engaging music)
- Sir, you're gonna have to
put your clothes back on.
- [Presenter] The Public,
buy or rent today and watch
anytime, anywhere on your
favorite screen to a DIRECTTV Cinema.
Movies start at channel 125.
- [Presenter] Get started
for just five bucks.
(engaging thing)
- One More Thing before we go.
Meet Cori Coco Gauff.
She's 15 years old.
Born in Atlanta she started
playing tennis at the age
of seven, inspired by who else,
Venus and Serena Williams.
After noticing that she had
a knack for it on the court
her family moved to Florida to give her
better opportunities to train.
By the time she was 11 she had the chance
to train with Serena
Williams' coach in France
and by 14 she had won her
first match as a professional.
Just a few months later she
was signed by New Balance.
Despite achieving so much
in her 15 short years
nothing could've prepared
her for what was to come.
First, came Friday when Coco
became the youngest person
to qualify for the main draw at Wimbledon.
She said right afterward that she hoped
that maybe she could play
against one of her idols.
So then came yesterday.
She took the court at
Wimbledon and on the other side
of the net, seven time Grand
Slam champion Venus Williams.
Coco's dream come true taking
on one of the few very women
who inspired her to pick up
a racket in the first place.
There they were, the
youngest at Wimbledon, Coco,
versus the eldest at
Wimbledon, Venus Williams,
39 years old, no one and I mean no one
could've predicted what this
15 year old would do next.
(ball thwacks)
(crowd cheers)
- [Announcer] A standing ovation.
Coco Gauff conquers Venus Williams.
- Just unbelievable.
Coco becoming the
youngest player since 1991
to win in the first round
of the women's tournament,
a rising star taking down
a titan in straight sets.
Coco, overcome with emotion
as you would expect,
her parents beaming with
pride from the stands.
So what does a teen star tell her idol
after besting her in
front of the whole world?
- After the match I told her
just thank you for everything
she did, I wouldn't be
here if it wasn't for her.
- Indeed, a fun fact for you you.
In 2004, the year that Coco--