- No, this is just who has the most,
remember they wanted to do a smaller deal.
- But they probably,
we heard Adrian talk about
it, there's no interest.
When there's no interest
guess what kind of deals
are available to you?
The minimum exception,
so we might as well
put all 30 teams there.
- Right, no, that's very interesting.
Well, we're gonna have to see.
We might know more by tonight, right?
Could know about Kawhi by tonight,
could know about Boogie by tonight.
Come hang out with us,
7:00 Eastern on ESPN.
Until then watch your phones
'cause it's free agency.
Lots going on.
- Come on U.S. team,
let's do it.
(upbeat music)
- Coming up on this Tuesday
edition of NFL Live,
Juju Smith-Schuster joins us.
He'll talk about taking over
the Steeler's top receiver
and what his relationship with
Antonio Brown looks like now.
We highlights some of the NFL stars
that are nominated for ESPYS,
including a look back at Drew Brees'
record-breaking Monday
night football performance.
Plus, we hand out our
own award for the player
with the best highlights,
Patrick Mahomes, Sequon,
or Kyler in the running,
who will be crowned your highlight king?
Happy to have you with us
on this Tuesday afternoon,
holiday week.
Wendy Nix, Dianna Russini,
Victor Cruz and Mike Tannenbaum.
We will start with news regarding Cowboys
running back Ezekiel Elliot.
Zeke is once again headed
to the commissioners office.
The Dallas Cowboys running back
expected to meet with the
commissioner Roger Goodell today
in New York City regarding
a May incident in Las Vegas.
The meeting comes after an incident
at a Las Vegas music festival in May
in which Elliot had a
confrontation of sorts
with a security guard.
He was briefly detained but never arrested
or charged in the incident.
Nevertheless the Commissioner
wants to here him out,
hear what happened, Diana,
what more can you tell us?
- At this point right now
we don't know what exactly
is going on in that meeting
but they are meeting in Manhattan
to discuss Zeke's behavior
in that Las Vegas incident.
Jerry Jones, of course, has
stood by his running back,
saying that he doesn't see anything wrong
with what he saw on video tape.
Again, Zeke was in those handcuffs
and then those handcuffs were removed.
He was not charged, he
could still face punishment
if Goodell decides that he violated
the league's personal conduct policy
and that's what this meeting is to discuss
but as of now we are not
sure what the future holds
but those that I've spoken to
with the Cowboys organization,
strongly feel confident
that Zeke will not face
a suspension in this
because of this incident.
- Mike as a DM I know you had players
who had face-to-face meetings
with the commissioner,
who had hearings or due
diligence, if you will.
What's your take on the process?
- Yeah, despite how the
Cowboys are feeling,
a suspension certainly is in play.
We have to remember under
the personal conduct policy,
a player can be suspended
even though there may
not be criminal charges
and the fact that Ezekiel
Elliot is meeting in person
with the Commissioner signals
to me that a suspension,
albeit one game, two games,
could be in play here
and he was sent to New York for a reason.
So, we'll see how it plays
out in the coming days
but his prior behavior will certainly
be a factor in their assessment.
- Well let's shift gears
to between the lines.
Victor, how important is the running game
to this current Dallas Cowboys team?
- It's huge, especially
Ezekiel Elliot, right?
He's been the focal point of that offense,
especially from the
running back perspective,
year in and year out.
Things he can do with
the ball in his hands
whether out in space or just
handing him the football
behind that fantastic offensive line.
I mean, he is in my opinion
the heartbeat of that offense.
Obviously Dak is the leader
but Ezekiel's the one that makes them go.
As he does well, then you
got the play-action pass
and everything compliments the
attributes of Ezekiel Elliot,
so, obviously if he's there to miss
any significant amount of time, you know,
the Cowboys would be
looking to replace that,
those statistics and those numbers
that he puts up week in and
week out in a different way.
- Yeah, and Vic you just
hit the nail on the head.
When you look Dak
Prescott, his pass rating
goes from 97 to 122 play-action compared
to traditional drop-back.
So you can see the importance
of the running game.
Ezekiel Elliot, obviously
opposing defenses
are focusing in on stopping Ezekiel Elliot
and that's a very impactful,
in terms of his impact
on Prescott's production
to go from 97 to 122.
That's a huge jump in terms of
his play-action productivity.
- Huge jump and we'll
talk about Dak's deal
and when it may get done
but I'd be interested to
see how all of you feel
like this Dallas Cowboys team
stacks up in the division.
- I think they're right there at the top.
I think they're competing, obviously them
and Philadelphia are
right there neck and neck
and gonna be battling it
out throughout the season
but I think that they got all the tools.
When you look at them defensively
from the defensive line all
the way back to the secondary,
they're loaded at each position.
And then offensively like
we just talked about,
Dak Prescott, Ezekiel
Elliot, Martin Cooper,
Randall Cobb, Jason, I could
go on for days with this
but they have all of the talent.
- [Mike] Receivers.
- [Victor] Exactly.
We got all of the talent,
and not to mention
- [Wendy] They have a
new offense coordinator
- [Victor] In Clamor obviously.
Which obviously comes from college
and doing those different things.
So, he'll provide some creativity
that we probably haven't
seen and some different type
of plays that we haven't seen necessarily
from the Dallas Cowboys.
- You're not going with the Eagles,
you're going with the Dallas
Cowboys to win that division?
- Yes, unfortunately, nobody
in New York kill me please
but I'm going with the Cowboys
- Right, that was Victor.
When does Dak's deal get done?
Do we see that done before
the start of the season?
- I think that deal will get
before the start of the season.
In fact, even just talking to people
in the Cowboys organization
about the timing of it.
It's funny 'cause just a few months ago
the way it was being explained to me
it was gonna be a while.
It wasn't gonna get done.
And now it seems that I'm not sure
where the pressure is coming from.
I don't know why why they're
feeling the pressure.
But in terms of trying to get that done
it seems that that's gonna
be a priority for Dallas.
- You know the pressure really comes from
what Dak Prescott's
draft day disappoint was
is now becoming the reality
of a free agent opportunity
because he was not a first round pick.
Which was a disappointment.
But he's now in the final
year of his rookie contract.
So, unlike guys like Jared
Goff and Carson Wentz
who had the additional fifth year,
he could get to the market.
And he may not be a perfect player,
I'm a believer in Dak Prescott.
Not 'cause only what you do
from a passing standpoint
but the plays he makes with his legs.
If he made it to the open market
the way Kirk Hudson
did a couple years ago.
Hard to say what he could get
and I know people could say,
well, he could certainly get franchised.
But I could tell you from
an organization standpoint,
when you use the franchise tag,
the last position you wanna
use it on is the quarterback.
Because when you have a franchise tag
that means that the player
doesn't have to be there
for the off season program,
doesn't have to be
there for training camp.
He could come in the
Tuesday before opening day,
sign the tag, get paid
for the whole season
and it really puts the whole offense
and all those reps that you
don't have together Vic.
So, it's really a situation
where the sense of urgency Diana
in my mind it's coming from
the fact that this player
is 16 games away from
becoming a free agent.
- And then that quarterback
also feels that pressure.
I mean, and they don't ever
really feel like they belong.
Do you remember with the
Kirk Cousins situation
in Washington?
He was always out there proving
and proving and proving.
And I remember talking to him about it
and you could tell
- [Victor] It weighs on him
it was wearing on him
because he was like the
Washington Redskins organization
they were just looking to
date, and date, and date.
And he was looking for a ring.
He wanted to get married and
he wanted to feel that love,
and he never did.
For the Cowboys to put that on Dak,
that may not work out for them you know,
if they wanna make that work.
- You know what he's married to?
Money, a lot of money.
I am not crying for Kirk Cousins
but it is a point well made.
Alright, anyway.
Circling back to where we started,
and that is the Gillette.
The Cowboys certainly hoping
that he will not miss any time.
A video shows Browns running back.
Kareem Hunt being questioned by police
after an apparent incident Saturday night.
This was at a Cleveland bar.
The video published by TMZ Sports.
It shows Hunt speaking
with a number of officers.
He was not arrested, they
did not make a police report
regarding the incident.
This is according to a
spokesperson to Cleveland.com.
Still to come on NFL Live,
Steeler star wide-receiver Smith-Schuster,
he of Juju, joins us from
across the pond in London.
Find out what he's been up
to during the off season.
And the story of high
school football coach
born with one of the rarest
conditions in the world.
- There's definitely doubters
out there, like parents,
look at him, my son is
getting coached at quarterback
from a guy that has no arms and no legs.
That lights a fire under my butt
and probably gets me
excited to really just try
to prove people wrong about it.
- [Commentator] And another
golden moment from Wimbledon.
- That's the only circumstance
to which you would separate.
- Can't imagine doing it out the line.
- [Caitlin] This is Caitlin Dickerson
from the New York Times,
this isn't the only case.
Very little documentation.
I know that's not true.
And the shelter's really don't
know what to do with them.
I just got another person
from DHS to confirm this.
I have this number, we're
gonna publish this story.
♪ Take your time ♪
♪ Build a home ♪
♪ Build a place where we all can belong ♪
- [Narrator] Give extra, get extra.
With new Extra Refreshers gum.
- Look, make a wish.
- I wish for a biggie bag from Wendy's.
- I wish everyone loved
each other and was--
- That is a great wish Jimmy.
- [Narrator] Get a bacon double stacked
with a quarter pound of
fresh beef, nuggets, fries
and a drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
- [Narrator] The end,
mindlessly marches on.
Carrying up to 50 times its body weight.
It never questions the task at hand.
But this year, there's a more
thrilling path to follow.
- Kids! (car tires racing)
Change of plans.
- [Narrator] Defy the laws of human nature
at the Summer of Audi Sales Event.
Get exceptional offers now.
- I can't believe it.
- That I won the best of sweepstakes
and I get to be in this
Guy Cook commercial?
- Let's do the eyebrows first,
just tease it a little.
- Slather it all over, don't hold back.
- Well the squirrels
followed me all the way
out to California
and there's a very strange
badger staring at me.
- No, I can't believe how easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
my car insurance with GEICO.
- Where is the camel?
- Mr. Big Shot's got his own trailer.
♪ Roll out, rush in, drop back, defend ♪
- Believe it,
GEICO could save you 15% or
more on your car insurance.
- So I can buy from Enterprise Car Sales
and you'll take any trade in?
- That's right.
- Great!
There you go.
- Well it does need to be a vehicle.
- But I need this out of my house.
With a fair transparent value
for every trade-in,
Enterprise makes it easy.
- [Narrator] Discover a
new wave of refreshment
crafted using our unique
brew pure process.
White Claw Hard Seltzer.
Nothing tastes quite like it.
- We were all shocked that the
Odell contestants first pick
of the fantasy draft would be a rookie.
Who shaped your strategy?
- At this time--
- I'll take this one Lindsey
It's mine.
- The problem with Mahomes--
- I'm sorry, my lawyer says I
can't speak at this moment so.
- Honey Punchers and Mullets
is there any connection
between your attire and
you record last season?
- Oh no.
- [Narrator] Do you
take your fantasy draft
as seriously as we do?
Prove it for the chance
to have commissioner del
host your leagues draft
live at NFL headquarters.
- [Announcer] NFL Live is brought to you
by Nutro Wholesome Essentials pet foods.
Nutro, feed the clean.
And GEICO, 15 minutes could save you
15% or more on car insurance.
- [Wendy] Press coverage now
from our own Dan Graziano.
Sources, according to Dan,
CBA talks collective
bargaining agreement talks
between the NFL and players association
are expected to intensify
this summer in an effort
to get a new deal done by
the start of the 2019 season.
Three to four negotiating
sessions possible
in the month of July alone.
Former Packers wide receiver Randall Cobb,
signed by the Cowboys and free agency,
teamed up with Aaron Rodgers
for over 5000 receiving yards.
After being drafted by the pack in 2011,
he will face his former
team in week five in Dallas.
And he had to say this
about moving on from Green Bay
"It's like the ex-girlfriend
that broke up with you."
"When you see her five years later,"
"you hope you're in a better
situation than you were before"
"married, with kids,
and you're able to say,"
"yeah I did better without you."
You know what, he's right.
Nobody says that but
that's how everybody feels.
- But I don't think a breakup
has to be contentious.
- It doesn't matter, you know I don't care
if it's the best breakup
ever, you don't wanna be like,
oh life wasn't so great,
you're winning, I'm not.
No, you wanna win sorry.
It just is what it is.
Okay, anyway, that got us
thinking five years from now
who's better off.
Okay, we've seen a number of
NFL breakups, if you will.
So, again, five year mark, Randall Cobb
or the Green Bay Packers,
who's better off?
- I'm going with Randall Cobb,
I think he's joining a team in the Cowboys
that's a younger team.
I think they're an overall
better team right now
than the Green Bay Packers.
But I think in five years
he'll be in the playoffs
a couple times, he's obviously in the mix
of that wide receiving core,
he's gonna be a focal point
in that slot position.
That's an important
position nowadays in the NFL
and I think overall he'll just be better.
Dak Prescott's got a younger quarterback,
I think that'll serve him better
obviously giving that longevity
and be there for a couple years.
He can build that comradery
and that continuity with Dak
which will serve him
better five years from now.
- He's not gonna miss
Aaron Rodgers at all.
- They're a better overall team.
- (crosstalk drowns out speaker)
- All right listen, there
were no, in my opinion,
no more notable breakup than that one
between Odell Beckham Jr
and the New York Giants.
This one's easy if you talk about it now
but we're talking about
five years from now.
Diana who's better off?
- I'm gonna go with Odell Beckham Jr
is gonna be in a much better position.
Well first of all he got
paid, he got tons of money
and he has opportunity to make more money.
Price of living in Cleveland
is lower, taxes are lower.
So, from a personal financial standpoint
Odell Beckham Jr is winning big time.
But when it comes to football,
there is no quarterback
that I believe has more potential
to be one of the greatest
than I believe in what
Baker Mayfield could do
in terms of the continuity and the team
that they're building in Cleveland
compared to what they're
doing in New York.
We're not sure what's gonna
happen to Pat Shurmur,
if he's gonna be there,
you have to feel like
he could be on the hot seat
this year if it doesn't work.
It seems that Cleveland
is a much better off space
for Odell Beckham Jr.
So I think he's gonna look back and go,
you know what, that was good.
- That was good.
What's interesting is, the
Giants had a couple of breakups
also Landon Collins who's
better off in five years.
- I'm gonna go the other way here Diana,
I'm gonna go with the New York Giants,
Dave Gettleman and that front office.
When we look at what they've already done
to replace Landon Collins,
they acquired Antoine
Bethea in free agency
and Jabrill Peppers that
was part of the trade
that sent Odell Beckham Jr to Cleveland.
And although Collins is a good player,
I thought he was more productive
closer to the line of scrummage.
When you look at the way Peppers plays
he could replace him, he's
younger, more athletic,
and less expensive.
So, Wendy it's not five years.
We know right now we're
better off without Landin.
- Wow alright, fair enough, noted.
You know I said there
was no bigger breakup
but as soon as I said that
I thought about AB and the Steelers.
I'm gonna retract that.
But anyway, Antonio
Brown and the Steelers.
This one I think is tricky cause again,
you're talking about five
seasons out who's better off.
- I'm going with the Steelers here.
I really feel like the Steelers
organization as a whole,
they're gonna be turned the page fully
from the Antonio Brown drama,
they're gonna be lookin' at Juju.
He's gonna be tenured,
he's gonna be a true
veteran leader on that team.
Understand who he is.
Big Ben, who knows how
many years he has left?
But with that body frame and
if he takes care of himself
he can still be there five years from now
playing at a high level.
But these guys are ready to play.
I think as a team, as a perspective,
once they get rid of the drama
and get rid of the negativity
that's around that was
surrounding the team
with Le'Veon Bell and all of these things.
I think five years from now,
this team will be better
and Roethlisberger will be relaxed
and the team will be good to go.
- Alright, perfect segue,
how about Le'Veon Bell and
the Pittsburgh Steelers?
- Well I think we saw a little bit
of a sneak preview the last year right?
You know, Bell was a Steeler
- Not really.
- But he really wasn't,
so, we're gonna go with
the Pittsburgh Steelers
and obviously we're
talking about James Conner,
who filled in last year for Le'Veon Bell.
We have another year with him
now in the off season program
and I think really where
we're gonna miss Bell guys
isn't as a rusher but as a receiver.
But James Conner is a
really good running back,
he's productive between the tackles,
he's a good pass protector.
And again, another year
of growing into the job
I think Pittsburgh year in and year out
does a great job of letting guys move on.
I think the replacing
Bell, I agree with Victor
and I think they're gonna replace AB,
and I think they're gonna
replace Bell very well
with James Conner.
- Alright, I do think that team
has sort of rallied
around these departures.
That's now, we'll see where
they are in a few seasons.
This last one, I don't even think
you can count it as a breakup.
I'm not sure they even really dated.
I don't know, they went out.
- It was a hookup.
- It was a hookup, Josh
Rosen and the Cardinals.
- I think Josh Rosen
is gonna be better off.
Look, this kid had the weight
of the world on his shoulders.
He was a top draft pick, he
was supposed to be the savior,
the answer to the Arizona
Cardinals organization.
Of course, that didn't work
out so here he is in Miami now.
The pressure is really off.
He's got a new head coach here,
they're gonna be running
a new England system.
By the way, if you run the
new England offensive system
you've gotta be a smart guy.
That's what Josh Rosen is.
He's a smart guy and I think
he's gonna fit in well there
and it's gonna be a place.
And by the way, he also
had Fitzpatrick behind him
who doesn't really seems
to have the attitude
of a starter that doesn't want to help.
So, you have two smart
guys in a quarterback room,
it seems like that's a much better place
for Josh Rosen to flourish.
- But Diana, what about Kyler Murray,
you don't think Arizona with Kyler Murray
has a chance to be a dynamic
play maker five years from now?
- That's really what
this question is right.
Is an assessment of Kyler
Murray in a lot of ways.
- No it definitely is.
Again, the big question mark of course
is is it gonna work with Kliff Kingsbury.
But to me, my biggest issue with Arizona,
is last year and this year
is their offensive line.
So, as much as we can
say Kyler Murray can--
- I've got five years to fix it (laughter)
- Try'na get rid of me?
We got five years I'm just--
- Breaking up is hard to do.
- You gave us five years right?
- I gave you five years I did
- That's a lot of drafts.
- Fair enough.
Alright, when we come
back Juju Smith-Schuster
isn't thinking five years,
he's thinking right now.
And we'll talk roll models and
Steeler's culture coming up.
- Hi I'm Juju Smith-Schuster,
and I'm gonna tell you how much fun
I'm having this off-season.
(upbeat music)
- Remember that degree
you got in taxation?
Of course you don't because you didn't.
Your job isn't understanding tax code,
it's understanding why that
will get him a body like that.
Move. That.
Your job isn't doing hard work.
Here, it's making her do hard work
and getting paid for it.
- [Narrator] Snap and sort your expenses
to save over 4600 of tax time.
- Jody, it's time to get yours.
- [Narrator] QuickBooks, backing you.
- [Chance Voiceover] Flaming hot nacho,
they made the original hot hot.
♪ Hello ♪
♪ Shake up my hot flamers
and mix em with Doritos ♪
♪ Why all these people in my face ♪
♪ Wanna be my ace, wanna be my amigo ♪
♪ Hello ♪
♪ Talkin 'bout how far back we go ♪
♪ Way way way back ♪
♪ I don't care about that ♪
♪ I aint sharing my snacks ♪
- I made this for you.
- Wonderful.
(audience applauding)
- Now it's hot
- Not running. Why am I not running?
Because the new DQ sour Blizzard menu
is only here for a few more weeks
with seven great flavors
like new sour patch
kids and Brownie dough.
- Not running.
- [Narrator] DQ, happy tastes good.
(grill sizzling)
(music)
- [Narrator] Tegate, bold on the outside,
light on the inside.
- [Narrator] How do you gage
the greatness of an SUV.
Is it to carry cargo?
Or to carry on a legacy?
Is it its design of strength,
or its sign of intelligence?
In crossing harsh terrane,
or breaking new ground?
This is the time to get
an exceptional offer
on the Mercedes of your mid-summer dreams
at the Mercedes-Benz Summer Event.
Going on now.
Lease the GLA 250 SUV
for just $329 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz Summer Event.
Mercedes-Benz, the best or nothing.
- [Narrator] Exclusively
on ESPN plus, UFC 239.
She's the first woman in UFC
history to hold two title belts
now coming off a stunning victory.
Rising star Amanda Nunes
is said to defend her Bantamweight title.
Find on ESPNplus.com/PPV.
(music in Spanish)
- [Narrator] Men, wanna feel
younger, stronger, leaner?
You don't have to slow down after 40.
Frank Thomas found the
secret of staying in shape,
with the energy and drive of his 20s.
Man you look like you
could still hit it a mile.
- I feel great too.
- What gives?
- After 40, men slow down,
it's harder to stay in shape.
- Why?
- Our free testosterone levels drop.
It happened to me and then
I found Nugenix Total-T.
- [Narrator] New Nugenix
Total-T is our most powerful
man-boosting formula ever
because it boosts your free testosterone
and your total testosterone.
Nugenix Total-T helps provide
even more energy, performance,
testosterone and muscle
boosting ingredient
for even better results.
To get you complimentary
bottle of Nugenix Total-T
text tie to 321321.
Samples are not available in stores.
- Why wait when you could
do something about it now.
- I gotta try Nugenix Total-T.
- [Narrator] Text TIE to 321321 now
for your complimentary
bottle of Nugenix Total-T.
That's TIE to 321321.
- [Narrator] Throw along pal.
- Is this really the emaculate
reception football lives,
or is running out of
bounds ever and option?
- No no no.
- Whenever I say we're gonna win the game
I guarantee you I meant it.
- The 1920s started the NFL.
- Quit looking at my chest
hair, look at the play.
- Keep them white legs up.
(upbeat music)
- [Commentator] That
is Juju Smith-Schuster,
Smith-Schuster past midfield.
- [Commentator] Leap and
grab by the man called Juju.
- [Commentator] Juju at the
back of the end zone, wow!
- We're joined this afternoon
by Juju Smith-Schuster
who's making his way all
the way across the atlantic.
He is in London this
afternoon for the NFL Academy
where he's an ambassador.
Juju tell us exactly what that is
and what it means there in London.
- So here in London
we're working with the NFL Academy.
Which is an amazing thing
because the opportunities to players.
Young players from the age 15 and up.
You know, who learnt the
new game, American football.
This is new to them.
Which is awesome.
But it's awesome because it
just gives them the opportunity
that they have another
career, another goal
that they can set to play in
the states and to play NFL.
- Juju we talked to
James Conner yesterday,
he talked about turning
the page about the changes
that had gone on in Pittsburgh
during the off season.
What's the temperature of this team
as you get ready for training camp?
- We're out in the 70, we're not too cold
or we're not too hot,
so, the weather is really nice right now.
In our locker room everyone
is on the same page you know.
Focusing on the same goal.
Which is amazing, because
that's what we're all about.
Is we're all about the
team, there's no individuals
and we're here to win games
and win championships.
- Juju talk to me about some of the talent
you're seeing out there in London behind.
Are there an Ballers out there,
any future Steelers out there or what?
- Oh man, there's some talent
out here, some potential.
I mean, you gotta understand,
this game is new to them.
You know, we started
lifting weights at 14,
these guys are barely starting at 16, 17.
So if we were to get
them on the right page
on to the academy, that
would be amazing to
start a team.
Eventually start their
middle school, high school,
and that would be their academy.
- Alright Juju it's been well documented
that Antonio Brown is no
longer with the Steelers,
now you're the number one guy.
How does it feel?
Do you feel a difference
in the locker room?
Are people treating you differently?
Are dudes getting your
lunch trays for you,
like is it a different feeling
being the number one guy?
How does it feel?
- Nah man there's no difference.
I mean all the people used to say,
you're the number one guy this year
but more for myself man I
just see it more opportunity
for not just myself but
for other guys to step up.
You're talking about AB
having a hundred catches
over a thousand yards.
Those yards, those catches
are gonna be spread out
you know obviously between
James Conner, Vance McDonald,
and James Washington, Donte Moncrief,
a lot of guys, James Samuels.
There are so many guys who
are gonna get more touches,
more catches, more yards, more yak.
You know, just to help them individually.
But at the end of the day
I'm still the same dude,
same Juju, same person, I'm
just last year I was 21,
this year I'm 22, same thing.
- [Victor] That's what's up.
- [Wendy] The 22 year old
version of Juju Smith-Schuster,
Juju you reference the
football being spread around,
that makes the communication
with Ben Roethlisberger
all that more important.
What's your relationship
like with your quarterback?
- It's amazing man, you know what I mean,
Ben he's a great leader, great dude,
he's taken the whole offensive group
down to his lake house in Georgia.
Amazing, we spent time together bonding,
we worked hard, we threw
but at the end of the day
it's more so like building
that bond and that connection
and what he did for us was amazing.
I think it's so crazy that a guy
who's been in the league
for like 15, 16 years
he sees so many guys come and go
and you know for me I'm only 22 years old,
when I met him I was 20 years old
and our bond is just gonna keep growing.
- I know as a athlete,
as a super star athlete that you are
you're always working on something new.
You're always working on something
new to perfect your game.
Give me one thing you've been
working on this off season
to just either get better at
or something you wanna add
to your game, or whatever the case may be.
- Man I've been really
really focusing in playing
more inside and outside and
learning the whole package.
Learning the whole offense,
that's what separates being
on the field the whole game
than being on the field
certain plays during packages.
I think it's great that I'm
able to play outside, inside,
right side, left side, inside in.
That's gonna help out a lot,
that's something I've
really been focused on,
it's just studying that
playbook till the next level
and understanding what
everybody has on the field.
- Juju we also get to see
everything else you do via social media.
Does anybody in the NFL
have more fun than you do?
- Not necessarily, I mean
I do lots of YouTube stuff
there's a lot of stuff I do on that end.
I really love to show my personal side.
You know, my fun side,
what I do in my free time,
you know playing Fortnite.
I do a lot of video-game
streaming, Twitch,
and making YouTube videos.
I think a lot of guys in the NFL
they just post a lot
of working out videos,
which is nothing wrong with that
but what do they like to
do on their free time?
Do they like to travel the world?
Do they like to just
stay home watch movies?
I think a lot of their
fans would love to see that
on a more personal base.
- Well, and some like
to go to prom you know.
Which apparently you did recently.
Tell us about the prom.
- So the prom was awesome, you know.
A kid, he's from PA Pittsburgh.
Ideally he wanted to take
this girl that he liked a lot
and his best friend ends up taking her.
He told his best friend
too but his best friend
kind of went behind his
back, took his girl.
So he asked me and I was just like, man
let's just one-up this kid.
We buy a suit, we get a party bus,
we basically stole the night
away from him and his girl
but at the end of the day
we all had a good time.
I met the guy, he seems like
a good kid, so he's great.
My friend is great
'cause he got like 20k followers, Anthony.
So he's super excited about
his college career coming.
- Anthony one, friend and
girlfriend nothing, he wins.
- Juju we saw you getting
busy on the dance floor.
We saw you getting busy on
the dance floor right there.
Talk to me about what
celebrations you got in store.
I know you're always being creative,
you always bring some
new stuff to the table.
What you got in store for us this year
from the celebration standpoint?
Man so look, I'm super excited.
Yes, I'm a young dude in
a room but I'm very vocal,
it's my time to step up, to be a leader
and what I mean by leader, I'm
getting everybody on the page
to do major celebration Marlon McCree,
he's older than me but he's
gonna do these celebrations.
James Washington.
All these guys, major celebration.
James Washington's on the same page
because we're in the same class.
And then I'm still working
on Big Ben and Alejandro.
They're a lot older than me
so they've been there before
so we'll see how it all figures out.
But major celebrations coming soon.
- All right, we can't wait.
Last question, we asked
James Conner this yesterday
to close things out,
why should Steeler fans
be optimistic as we look toward 2019?
- Man Steeler fans they're
always here supporting
since day one whether
we're doing good or bad,
I don't doubt those supporters to the end.
I'm kind of happy where
we're at right now,
we're not the headline, the Browns,
the team that everyone is watching
what kind of noise they're gonna make.
I'm super excited to watch them play too.
Seeing OBJ comment on my post
and I'm commenting on his post
like, yo we can't wait who's
gonna have the best dance moves
but like I said this year
the fans just support
until the end because
we're gonna finish strong.
You always notice we always pull through.
- [Wendy] Alright Juju, best of luck.
We appreciate you being with us.
- [Victor] Thanks for being with us Ju.
- Thank you, I appreciate it.
- [Wendy] With Antonio Brown
now departed to Oakland,
Juju will become Big
Ben's number one option
and he should receive tighter coverage.
Over the last two seasons
been facing press covers.
Juju actually though
had a better catch rate
and yards for target than Antonio Brown.
Clearly Victor perspective changes
a little bit I would think.
You know he's the number one
guy, he can say whatever.
What kind of pressure?
How is it different for
Juju starting this season
than say last year?
- I think the only thing
different is like you said,
the mindset, the perspective,
obviously you're coming
into that locker room
and Antonio Brown is
not there, it's just you
and now you become kind of that leader.
People are looking to you.
You've been there, you
understand who you are.
I know you're just 22 years old
but now you become the guy
that the younger teammates
are looking up to you
wanting to know what you're doing,
wanting to hang out with
you in the off season.
Wanting to just steal a little
bit of knowledge from you.
Your relationship with Ben.
They wanna get a headstart
on what they need to do to get better
and he becomes the guy that
leads the charge in that regard
and it's pretty big shoes to fill.
And I think the Steelers
have done a great job.
I think they were preparing
for this for a number of years.
And there is that whole notion
of we have to win for today
and develop for tomorrow.
And you look at that
position in that organization
going back to Mike
Wallace, Santonio Holmes,
obviously Antonio Brown, Smith-Schuster.
They do a great job of
getting guys in the pipeline,
getting them developed.
And now Antonio Brown moves on,
Smith-Schuster steps up
to be the number one guy.
I think they've done
a remarkably great job
for a number of years.
Especially at this position.
- I Think that's a great
point, and I would argue
that outside of New England,
they probably do it as well as anybody
in terms of continuity.
I know Antonio Brown ended in a way
they probably didn't anticipate
but they did anticipate
that it would end at some point.
And to that end, and
Mike to you your point,
they seemed to be sort of in lockstep
for planning for the future.
- I think there's three things
that Juju Smith-Schuster
has to probably focus on this season.
It's going from being a great
receiver to an elite receiver.
He needs to play at that level.
Victor touched on the leadership aspect.
It's obvious just from that interview
you can hear he has stepped
up to already be the leader.
He's talkin' 'bout trying to get Big Ben
in the offensive line
to participate in his celebration drills.
And they obviously have
good chemistry there.
And then that third
layer is being a mentor
to those younger guys.
So he's gonna be asked a lot more of him
as a football player out on the field
and of course in the locker
room, but if there's one thing
I think we've learned
about Juju over the years
is he attacks everything with open arms.
He is an open book himself,
he embraces that role
and he wants to be that character guy.
He wants to be that good guy.
And when you talk to
players on the Steelers
about Juju Smith and what
his personality is like
because obviously on social
media he's so much fun
and he can be loud,
apparently he does a lot
of his work silently.
He's not the loudest guy in the room,
he's not the one joking
around during drills.
He likes to have fun but
he is locked in and focused
and I think if he can take
his game to that elite level
the Antonio Brown conversations
that we're gonna be having
are gonna feel so long ago.
- You know what else he said
that was really impressive
in the interview,
he touched on at the end about
the Steelers are always there in the end.
And it's not where you start in football,
it's where you end.
And you look at Pittsburgh
and New England,
those teams always improve
during the course of the season.
So, James Conner,
Smith-Schuster in a new role.
It's not what they look
like August or September.
Are they ascending and getting better
and Mike Tomlin deserves so much credit.
The player development, the
way they couch their players.
They get better and I thought
his point was a good one
which is, hey, we'll be there in the end
because that's where they've
been year in and year out.
- It almost feels like they transform
and they kinda morph into
whatever they need to be to win
towards the second half of the season
and that's what keeps them in
the hunt year in and year out.
- Well, and I understand
for all kinda reasons
why everybody's looking to Cleveland.
But I think you'd unwise
to sleep on Pittsburgh
in any way, shape, or form.
Mike Tomlin as the head
coach, a veteran squad.
This is a good team.
I think that you could argue
underachieved last season.
We'll see.
What do Patrick Mahomes, Sequon Barkley
and Kyler Murray all have in common?
They make head turning,
highlight real worthy plays.
We'll crown the highlight king next.
- You ever watch like the
highlights on YouTube?
- [Commentator] Patrick Mahomes on fire.
- [Commentator] Looks one
way, zings in another.
- [Commentator] There you go!
- [Commentator] Fly's over the top, flips
and goes around, touch down.
- [Commentator] Kyler
Murray an absolute dime!
- [Commentator] He's the best
quarterback you'll ever see
at everything else except height.
- [Commentator] Patrick
Mahomes with Mahomes magic.
How did he pull that off!?
- [Narrator] If only
there was a place nearby
you can get one of these or these.
Good thing they're sold
everywhere business is done.
I'm pretty sure you
can buy them at a bank.
Not sorry, Reese's.
(upbeat music)
♪ Summer nights keeping me up ♪
♪ I wanna waste time
just lookin' up the sky ♪
♪ Fallen stars, mind wandering far ♪
♪ Like we're sixteen
dreamin' in the dark ♪
♪ Love the wind in my
hair as I drive my car ♪
♪ It makes me feel free ♪
- [Narrator] Now get exceptional offers
at the Infinity + Summer Sales event.
- [Narrator] Too many people in pain
settle for a restless night's sleep,
there's a better choice.
Aleve pm, the only one to
combine a safe sleep aid
and the 12 hour pain-relieving strength
of a leave that dares to
last into the morning.
So you feel refreshed.
Aleve pm, there's a better choice.
♪ La la la la la la ♪
- [Narrator] Home, it's
so much more than a house,
it's your own freshly cut fairway.
For over 30 years Rocket Mortgages helped
millions of Americans finance
the home of their dreams.
- Nope, nope.
- [Narrator] So you can focus
on making your house home.
Rocket Mortgage, push
button, get mortgage.
- [Narrator] What does it
take to burn one calorie
and enjoy the great taste of Miller lite?
A walk to the bar.
More taste is worth one more calorie.
What are you holding?
Miller lite, hold true.
- [Blonde Woman Voiceover]
Thanks Golden Corral,
Dan gets a slow smoked sirloin
and my little trio are as happy as shrimp,
oops, clams.
And mom, got it all,
hook line and sirloin.
The slowest smoked
sirloin and shrimp trio.
Golden Corral, the only one for everyone.
(suspension music)
- Stop the car!
Stop the car!
- [Narrator] The IKEA Summer Sale.
Save up to 50% off select
items in store only
June 26 to July 7, IKEA.
- [Trainer] Alright, we're in
this together, one more time.
Three, two rise with me.
Make every step a little
stronger than the last.
- [Narrator] Over 90
live classes every week.
Just one part of the best
cardio machine on the planet.
Peloton.
- Hi, Phil Swift here.
People everywhere tell me how much
they love the Flex Seal
family of products.
- This stuff is awesome.
- It really works.
- Best stuff I ever got.
- [Narrator] Nothing
compares to the strength
of original Flex Seal.
Like Seal liquid, Flex Shower,
Flex tape and Flex glue.
Use the Flex Seal family of
products to weather-proof
and protect virtually everything.
From your home, car and
truck, to your boat and RV.
Seal up gaps, cracks and holes.
Patch busted pipes.
Seal gushing gutters.
Even make quick repairs underwater.
Now you can make
emergency roadside repairs
in the toughest conditions.
All Flex Seal products create
a super strong water-tight barrier.
Now you can coat, patch, seal and repair.
- Imagine everything you could do
with the Flex Seal family of products.
- [Narrator] available
at these fine retailers.
- Guys, how frustrating is it
to find a great pair of
jeans too tight here,
too loose there, too long there.
Standard jeans use just two measurements,
and MTailor custom jeans use
seven different measurements
to give you the perfect fit.
Your phone can measure you right now.
Download the MTailor
app on IOS or android,
choose from hundreds of styles.
Mtailor measures you digitally
and is 20% more accurate
than a professional tailor.
With free shipping and
a money back guarantee
get your new favorite pair of jeans today.
Mtailor, available on the
Apple App Store or Android.
- [Announcer] With the first pick,
the New Orleans Pelicans
select Zion Williamson.
The New York Knicks select RJ Barrett.
- [RJ] Yo I love the bigger
stage, I love the challenge
- [Zion] My dreams came
true, I'm just ready to work.
- [Wendy] MBA Summer
League action on Friday.
Triple header starting
at 7:30 Eastern on ESPN.
You don't wanna miss a
special matchup at 9:30
featuring former Duke
teammate Zion and RJ Barrett
facing off for the first
time in the association.
Press coverage now from
our own Josina Anderson.
An update, the NFL and
NFLPA have already scheduled
CBA negotiating sessions for
July 17 through the 19th.
It will be the first
time both sides engage
in talks for three consecutive days
specifically on this pending league deal.
Dan Graziano also reporting there
is hope of getting a new CBA
by the start of the 2019 season.
- [Diana] Great news.
- [Wendy] Let's take a
look at a few NFL players
nominated for the ESPYS shall we?
- After an impressive
sophomore running through
for over 5000 yards and 50
touch downs and won an MVP.
Patrick Mahomes nominated
for best male athlete.
Sequon Barkley nominated for
the best breakthrough athlete.
Last season Barkley burst out of the scene
rushing for 1307 yards.
Broke a giant record.
Kyler Murray nominated
for best college athlete.
He became the seventh
to win the highest man in OU's history.
None of those are too shabby alright?
Today we give out the
Highlight King award.
Is that in ESPY or it's not?
- It is not but--
- Could be
- It should be.
- It definitely should be but it's funny
because my choice is
Kansas city quarterback
Patrick Mahomes.
He is up for male athlete of the year
- But you're crowning
him the Highlight King.
- He's getting my vote, and here's why.
Against the Ravens, facing fourth and nine
from the chiefs forward,
Mahomes just did what we had
seen him do countless times.
Which was buy time with his feet.
- [Mike] Get outta bounds.
Relies on his right hand there,
finds Tyreek Hill down field
and the best part is after
the game Andy Reid said,
oh yeah that's exact how you decided.
Yeah, sure Andy.
How about against the Broncos?
We knew his right hand was magical.
Did you just say lucky?
- [Narrator] Leftie.
- Oh I thought you said lucky, I was like,
I don't think that was luck right?
We knew his right hand was pretty magical
but his left hand here.
Spots Von Miller comin right at him.
- [Mike] Semi-spiral on that.
- [Diana] Even when you're defense
is doing everything they should be doing.
There are situations where
you cannot beat Pat Mahomes
because he comes up with some
unthinkable moments here.
His athleticism, his vision of the field,
and his ability to stay
in the pocket plays
and of course outside the pocket
is where his perhaps
probably most dangerous.
- Alright I'm going with
Sequon Barkley here.
- [Wendy] Oh wait, he's your
Highlight King just to be clear
- He is my Highlight King Sequon Barkley
because he is a highlight machine
as you can see he's
broken at least 47 tackles
on that one to get to the end zone.
In this one I mean, he's just
putting his foot in the ground
he will not be denied against Philadelphia
obviously a rivalry in that division.
And he's taken off on that one.
In this one, this one's pretty good.
Okay we know this guy is good.
First of all tremendous
block by 73 right there
but this run is just indicative
of the type of athlete
that Sequon Barkley is.
He can shake guys behind
him, in front of him,
and he's got the speed to
outrun anybody in this league.
And that's what we see here.
And it's always on display.
And then I get a bonus Diana,
I get a bonus here like this one.
That's a little hurdle,
how many runner backs are doing that?
Not only a handful of guys
I can probably count 'em all
on one hand who can hurdle guys
in traffic like that and keep it moving.
- (crosstalk drowns out speaker)
- Protection two he was able
to, not to pile on your Giants.
But the fact that he was able
to do that with that
old Lion is incredible.
- [Wendy] Mike Tannenbaum.
- I got Kyler Murray, I was at this game,
his resiliency was unbelievable,
they got outplayed
badly in the first half.
He comes down in the second
half, he steps up with the Pak
he keeps his eyes down on the field,
that puts so much pressure on a defense.
Throws a really accurate pass.
This was a great play.
Got Oklahoma back in the game.
This was another game I was
at, West Virginia's defense
was horrific in this game.
If they were playing flag football,
Tyler Murray still
would've gone untouched.
- [Victor] Looks like flag football.
- And this is what Arizona was hoping for.
Look at how many guys he
can make miss in space
and then have the speed
to take it all the way.
The amount of pressure
he'll put on defenses
will be formidable in the fall
because it'll be his arm and his feet.
Speaking of his arm, look at this one.
Oklahoma state big rivalry game.
Again, 50 yards out in
the field Brown in stride.
This guy's gonna be a dynamic play maker.
He is a highlight machine, he
is the Highlight King maker
and Arizona Cardinals fans,
that's what they're looking
forward to in the fall.
- They're hoping, fingers crossed.
Listen, we told you we'd like to vote.
We narrowed the field.
It's one of these three
Highlight King okay.
So go to out Twitter handle @ESPNNFL,
you can vote one of these three
and we'll let you know what you think.
Also, by the way, while
you're at it don't forget
you can also vote on the ESPYS right now,
that is at ESPY.com
Diana you already voted.
- [Wendy] A man born without
arms or legs found his calling
coaching high school football.
- He comes out full head of
hair parted down the side,
I told him, there's
nothing ugly about him.
He's still an angel.
- What's up DK, I know
you're asking yourself,
am I worth the hype?
Can I live up to it all?
See that's the thing about hype,
it can make you or break you.
Here's what I've learned.
They get to ask all the questions,
but only you get to answer.
Good luck DK.
♪ Na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ eh eh eh goodbye ♪
- [Narrator] The world first
six-function multi-protal gate,
available only in the
next generation GMC seer.
Get 20% below MSRP next
generation 2019 GMC double cab
and SLE crew cable models
with the standard talegate.
- [Narrator] Why use
Post-it extreme notes?
Because they make your message stick,
getting it said and done
right the first time.
- Oh come on.
- [Narrator] Stop the re-work
with the Post-it extreme notes.
(phone ringing in distance)
- Looks like someone's still nervous
about buying a new house.
- Is it that obvious?
- Yes it is.
Or maybe you'd worry less if you GEICO
to help with your home owners insurance.
- I didn't know GEICO helps
with home owners insurance.
- Yeah, they've been doing it for years.
What are you doing?
Big Steve?
- Thanks man.
- There he is.
- [Narrator] Get to know GEICO
and see ow much you can save
on homeowners and renters insurance.
- [Narrator] Discover a
new wave of refreshment
crafted using our unique and pure process.
White Claw Hard Seltzer.
Nothing tastes quite like it.
- [Narrator] Takeru
Kobayashi, Joey Chestnut,
two record-setting champions.
- [Commentator] Kobayashi,
the dominant power
of this man may end the dynasty.
- We were pushing each other to limits
that neither one of us
thought we were gonna go to.
- We had a great rivalry.
- [Narrator] What if I told you
there was even more
beef behind the scenes.
- I didn't expect that it
would end the way it did.
- [Narrator] The Good,
The Bad, The Hungry,
tonight at 8pm on ESPN.
(upbeat bass guitar strumming)
- [Narrator] Why settle for ordinary
when you can have extraordinary
at Touchofmodern, watches
don't just tell time,
they change the way you spend it.
Bags are thoughtfully designed
to never slow you down
and gear won't get in the way.
And coffee tables are also refrigerators.
Keeping you at the center of the party.
All it takes is a touch.
Touchofmodern.com
- The ESPYS auction is
where you can bid on
once in a lifetime experiences,
like joining me on the
set of Sports Center.
That should be like a million dollars.
- Join me in Sunday night
baseball in the booth.
- You can join me and we'll
make a puppet in your likeness.
- Come and hang out with me
and my least favorite son
Dan on South beach.
- [Narrator] So bid now on Ebay.com/ESPN.
- [Wendy] The ESPYS auction
includes amazing experiences
across sports and entertainment
including those you just heard about.
Go to Ebay.com/ESPN to
bid now through July 10th.
All proceeds benefit the V
Foundation for cancer research.
We've been highlighting our ESPY nominees
throughout the show but this
one goes beyond football.
High school football coach Rob Mendez,
who will be the recipient
of the Jimmy V Award for perseverance.
Born with an extremely rare condition
that affects less than
100 people in the world.
Mendez found his calling coaching a sport
that he was never able to play himself.
- Essy( featured chronicles,
Mendez's first season as
a head football coach.
Capturing the inspiring and unlikely story
of a coach who transformed
a group of young athletes
from skeptics into believers.
(slow music)
- [Coach] At this time I
just wanna introduce to you
somebody that I think can really help
turn this program around.
A coach that I hired cause I was impressed
with his knowledge of the game.
His passion as a coach blew me away.
Everything else that's on top of that,
in terms of who he is and what he does
on a day to day basis,
inspires me.
Your new coach, Rob Mendez.
(deep music)
- It was awful, it was
really really awful.
I didn't have a choice to have an abortion
so, I had to keep Robert.
- In the back of mind
I'm asking, why my son?
You know, less than 100
born like him in the world.
What am I gonna do with this boy.
- It was hard to see him.
I really didn't wanna see Robert.
So I didn't see little
Robert for about two weeks
because I didn't know what to do.
- I just remember staring,
you know there was a lot of staring.
It would piss me off really bad.
Like he was not a human or something.
- But he is different,
he sees people staring as an opportunity.
- Things that you an I
get to do in ten minutes
might take him an hour but
he never complained about it.
- Robert was just a really easy child
and he just was really really happy.
- What's your favorite team?
San Francisco 49ers.
- He's got a gift that doesn't
require him to be physical.
Making him aware of that,
I think he just took the ball and ran.
- I think the most difficult part
about having no arms and no legs
is simply not being able to play sports.
I don't show it, I'm good at
not showing it but I get mad.
I get mad at God, I get mad at the Lord.
Like why?
- His freshman year, he was
standing behind the fence
at a distance watching the practice.
That was the beginning.
- We wanted to get him
involved in the program
so we invited him to be our manager.
- They didn't know what I could do,
they obviously knew I couldn't
play but just to include me,
it made me feel a part of it.
You know, it made me feel, I
guess you could say normal.
- He paid attention to us as coaches
but he learned the game
playing Madden football.
He created game plans on Madden
and then he'd come to
practice and try to create
the same game plans and
execute them the same way.
- I started giving Robert a
little bit more responsibility
with my quarterbacks.
And the next thing you know
he was there running the drills for us.
His ability to study the game
and his ability to translate
those things to the kids
is unmatched by most of
the coaches that I know.
- I've been overlooked,
the last three or four years
I've been ready for it.
When I go to a job interview
sometimes I feel like I'm gonna
scaring is not the right
word, surprise them.
And I don't know how they're
gonna take the surprise.
- As he rolls out, to be
brutally honest, when I saw that
I'm like how can this guy coach?
And as he comes close he
goes, give me a fist pump,
give me a fist pump.
I just gave him a little fist pump
right there on his shoulder
and all that nerves that
I had just melted away.
We had other applicants
but I knew in my heart
that it would be a great fit
for these young athletes.
- I remember when coach Kibble hired me,
cruising off the campus I
just felt really accomplished
'cause it took me so long I
knew I've been ready for it
and I've been overlooked.
And finally somebody
gave me the opportunity
so I really appreciated that.
- At this time I just
wanna introduce to you
your new JBL coach Rob Mendez.
(applause)
- Appreciate that coach Kibble
Thank you coach.
You know football is my passion,
this is gonna be my 13th year coaching
and I can't wait to get to
know every single one of you.
Believe in yourself,
believe in your teammates,
and believe in what you're doing.
Are we clear gentlemen?
I'm excited guys.
- Obviously it was a little shocking
and there was jokes coming around.
Typical teenagers you know
a guy with no arms or legs,
not a lot of people have seen that.
If you're taken aback that's
just natural and that's human.
But after the first two
seconds, it's just a normal guy.
- I don't care how good you are,
I don't care how experienced you are,
you guys are gonna do
everything as a team.
- Though he may not look like a coach,
he definitely acts like one.
- 9, 157, so what we're
gonna teach right now
is called 31 zone.
- His knowledge of the game
for somebody who actually
hasn't gone through it
is impressive.
On his phone he can diagram a play faster
than I can do it with pen and paper.
- There's definitely doubters
out there like parents.
Look at him, my son is getting coached
at quarterback by a guy who
has no arms and no legs.
That lights a fire under my butt
and probably gets me excited
to really just try to prove
people wrong about it.
Perfect! Good job!
- When they see him and
witness him, and hear him,
I'd like to believe
that they take a moment
to evaluate themselves
and anything that they've
gone through in life
can't be more difficult
than what he endures
on a daily basis.
- One thing I care
about more than anything
is being a family, that is
one thing I take pride on,
I love people.
I love you, I love you, I
love you, I love everyone.
So if you guys can't show
love on this football field,
then you better get off of it.
Towards you Aden, who am I gonna go to?
It was a fractured orbital bone
and my cheekbone is fractured as well,
I couldn't sleep, I couldn't chew.
- I just felt bad for him.
You know he's got a hard life
and I try to make it as easy as I can.
Things that you and I take for granted
like brushing your teeth
or washing your face
or taking a shower or
going to the restroom
Robert needs someone to help him.
But he's tough, two days
later he was at his practice.
And his thing is now I
gotta be there for the kids.
He's been waiting to be a
head coach for a long time.
- I didn't wanna let them down,
I didn't wanna let the kids down.
I just can't stay away I guess.
Me being challenged
has been my motivation.
All I gotta say is, who says I can't!?
- [Team] Nobody!
- Who says I can't!?
- Who says I can't,
originally came from me
just having a drive to accomplish
whatever people doubted me for.
Who says I can't!?
- [Team] Nobody!
- Who says I can't!?
- If he's willing to do all of that
then what are we willing to do?
(team chanting)
- It's go time, we've been
working hard all summer long.
Prospect on three, one two three.
- [Team] Prospect!
Go kick ass, let's go.
Those kids fought every single game,
I mean I can't remember one game
that we were bigger than the other team,
but dammit we got the job done.
That's what I'm talking about!
We got the momentum keep it up, lets go!
JBT in the last ten years has
had mostly losing seasons.
He just really has done a
job that I haven't been able
to see other coaches do
at that level before.
- I'm tryna send my Y over the middle
because it's gonna be
right here over the middle.
Give me a hug both of you guys,
appreciate guys, alright lets go.
- [Announcer] Good
morning and hello Prospect
and Soprano High, winner
today wins the league.
- Remember this, I'm proud
of every single one of you,
but dammit we're not done yet,
so let's go finish the job off right now.
- [Commentator] Might take a miracle plan
to score the only points in this contest.
Passes off to his right, intercepted.
4-37 play in the fourth quarter.
Soprano looking for the first points.
Kick on the way, has the distance,
and it's good and
Soprano takes a 3-0 lead.
- Let's just execute guys,
this is four league right here,
180 smash okay lets do it.
- [Commentator] Fourteen for
the panthers, fourth down
played Jackson off to his
left and it's incomplete.
Soprano gets the win and
cakes the division title.
What a win this afternoon over Prospect.
- Don't worry about it,
family is the most important
thing remember that okay.
That's what we built this
team off of was family okay.
You got good days and bad days man.
Today as a team it's okay,
I'm very proud of you,
the whole team.
It's gonna hurt today and
that's okay if it hurts
because we cared a lot.
Because we love this game of football.
I really sincerely want
you guys to understand
how much I appreciate this.
You guys have given me
a lifetime of memories.
- Our opponents they'd always doubt him
cause they see a man in a wheelchair,
to us we see our coach who's perfect.
- When we were pushing him
off the field after the game,
makes me feel proud to
have him as my coach.
- These kids would follow
him no matter where he go.
- You can actually see
the changes in the kid.
- Can I give you a hug?
- You want the best for your children.
I told him one time,
there's not a lot of money in this Robert
and he told me it's not everybody
who does what they do for money.
He's right.
- They give me the feeling of importance
and I don't think they know
that and understand that.
Maybe they will one day but
I love those kids
and I'm always gonna remember them.
I think we make a perfect
team, can we agree on that?
- [Team] Yes coach.
- Can we agree on that?
- Who says I can't!?
- [Team] Nobody!
- Well several schools
in the Silicon Valley
recently notified Mendez, a
varsity head coaching openings,
he's decided not to interview,
he says he has unfinished business
with his JV team at Prospect.
For more on Rob Mendez and
his remarkable journey,
head to ESPN plus for the
full half hour documentary
which you can stream right now.
And a reminder to catch
the ESPYS July 10th on ABC
to see Mendez receive the
Jimmy V Award for perseverance.
With AB now on the radars,
what might Juju's new role
be in Pittsburgh as
the lead wide-receiver.
We'll take up that topic next.
- [Narrator] Keep up
with your favorite team
on the go with the NFL app.
Get all your updates, scores
and live games during the season.
Download the NFL app from your app store.
- [Trump] Very very small
loan from my father.
- [Reporter] You've gotta start somewhere.
- [Reporter] A reporter
from the New York Times.
- [Reporter] Bank statements, tax funds,
property records of deeds.
- [Reporter] 1995 showed
that he was bleeding money
but through it all founded
it all number by number.
That's when we realized that's fraud.
- [Trump] I built this
empire, I did it by myself.
- Look, make a wish.
- I wish for a biggie bag from Wendy's.
- I wish everyone loved
each other and was--
- That is a great wish Jimmy.
- [Narrator] Get a bacon double
stacked with a quarter pound
of fresh beef, nuggets, fries and a drink
for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
- Ours is a proud bloodline,
we hail from the battlefields
to the bad lands.
from the mountains and the midtown's.
From the islands to the highlands.
And directly to those who understand
that when you get behind
a wheel of a Jeep Rangler
you're joining a family.
Hurry in to the 4th of July sales event,
get $500 additional bonus
cash on select models.
Visit Jeep.com
- [Narrator] What do you serve up
when that no name
charcoal burns out early?
Chicken tate?
Choose the charcoal worth
your flame, fastest lighting,
longest burning for the
way barbecue should taste.
Kingsford.
- [Narrator] With
worsening weather patterns,
an aging vulnerable power grid,
and the growing risk of cyber terrorism.
Power outages are a part of
life now, that can be stressful
because we depend on power more than ever.
When the power goes
out, we lose everything.
We can't even charge our smartphones.
Now more than ever,
you need a Generac automatic
home standby generator.
With prices starting at just $1,999
you can afford to always
have the power you need.
With Generac, power
stays on in your house,
even if you're not at home.
- I know that when the power goes out,
that Generac is gonna kick on
and I'm gonna have
power in my whole house.
- If it's out for 15 minutes or four days,
we're gonna be okay.
- We have control over what
happens in our lives now.
- Generac gives us that piece of mind
because it is our power grid.
- [Narrator] Call or go online
to schedule your free in-home assessment.
Generac has more than
5000 dealers nationwide.
That will help you select
a home standby generator
that will meet your needs
and fit within your budget.
They'll discuss installation
and provide you with a
comprehensive estimate.
It's a totally free assessment
with no obligation to buy.
Generac's automatic home standby generator
start at just $1,999.
Special financing is available
with affordable monthly payments.
Plus, with the Generac
mobile link, you can check
on your generator anytime
from anywhere in the world.
With the highest quality construction,
exceptional dependability and
state of the art technology,
it's easy to see why Generac
is the number one brand
of automatic home standby
generators in the world.
Call or go online to schedule
your free in-home assessment
and if you act right now,
you'll receive our 7 year
extended limited warranty.
A $695 value absolutely free!
Control your power and control your life
with a Generac automatic
home standby generator.
(orchestra music)
- [Commentator] Another
golden moment from Wimbledon.
- [Wendy] UFC 239 Saturday in Las Vegas,
two of the greatest champions
defending their titles.
Jon Bones battles Thiago Santos
and Amanda Nunes takes on Holly Holm
in the co-main events on Pay-Per-View.
That's starting at 10:00 Eastern.
Go to espnplus.com/payperview.
Juju Smith-Schuster
will enter training camp
as the Pittsburgh Steelers
number one wide-receiver
for the first time in his career.
Here is Smith-Schuster from earlier today
on what it's like on the expectations
of stepping into that role.
I mean all the people used to say,
you're the number one guy this year
but more for myself man I
just see it more opportunity
for not just myself but
for other guys to step up.
You're talking about AB
having a hundred catches
over a thousand yards.
Those yards, those catches are
gonna be spread out you know.
Obviously between James
Conner, Vance Donald,
and James Washington, Donte Moncrief,
a lot of guys, James Samuels.
There are so many guys who
are gonna get more touches,
more catches, more yards, more yak.
You know, just to help them individually.
But at the end of the day
I'm still the same dude,
same Juju, same person, I'm
just last year I was 21,
this year I'm 22 same thing.
- Yes, the older, wiser,
more mature 22 year old
Juju Smith-Schuster,
with a good yak reference,
always a good day.
- Alright listen, this
got us thinking obviously
big shoes to fill with
Antonio Brown deported.
He's now an Oakland Raider.
So, let's go one by one.
Receptions, more or less,
Antonio or Juju Mike?
- Juju just made all my points for me.
They're gonna spread the
ball around in Pittsburgh,
plus you have a head coach Jon
Gruden who's the play caller,
they gave up a lot of
money and picks to get EB.
EB will have more receptions.
- I do think Jon Gruden motivated
to get Antonio Brown the football.
How about touch downs Diana?
- Touch downs I'm gonna
go with AB as well.
You know you actually teamed
me up perfectly there Wendy
because I think if there
is anyone that wants
to make Antonio Brown work in Oakland,
cause they have to figure out
why the paid him all that
money, it's gonna be Jon Gruden.
So, he's obviously callin'
all the shots on offense here
and in terms of
wide-receivers in the game,
we can debate all long who is the best
but we all know how special AB can be.
And as soon as he can
figure out that chemistry
with Derek Carr I think he's
gonna have more touchdowns
than Juju does.
- All right, there's
receptions, there's touchdowns
and how about all purpose
yards Victor Cruz.
- I'm gonna give Juju some love here
because clearly Mike and Diana
did not give him any love so far.
But I'm going with Yards,
he's the bona fide number one guy now
which means in those pressure situations
Ben will be looking to him to
be that number one receiver
and get him the ball in space
either on drag routes, deep routes,
he could run any route in the book,
and it's gonna be interesting to see
just how they use him
as the number one guy.
- All right look, it's a team game
and all of those things are what they are.
But what really matters of
course, you hope anyway,
are the number of wins
from each of these teams.
We've got the Steelers,
we've got the Raiders.
Who gets the head cheer?.
- Yeah it's gonna be Pittsburgh.
I think we're gonna see an
improvement with Oakland,
especially in offense.
Josh Jacobs, Terrel
Williams, obviously AB,
another year with Derek
Carr and Jon Gruden.
Really worry about defense
and rushing the pass
but obviously they lost
Cleo Mack a year ago,
while they drafted Clelin
Ferrell from the first round.
It's gonna take a while
for him to get going.
I think they're gonna
be a working progress
in terms of how they are on defense.
I'm going with Mike Tomlin
and a very mature Pittsburgh
Steeler organization.
- I think that's a pretty good bet.
How about celebrations?
Is this even a question?
Well I guess maybe.
- It's not a question at
all, I'm going with Juju
mainly because it doesn't
even have to be him
that has to score to do the celebrations.
He's made that clear,
everybody is in on this thing,
so whether it's him or
whether it's Vance McDonald
or any other person on that team.
They're gonna be celebrating
and Juju will be leading the way.
- And let me tell you,
if you did not see it,
Juju was with us about an hour ago
and he said that he is
working on Ben Roethlisberger
to get him on.
He has not committed but he's trying.
- We'll see him in there.
- We'll see about that.
- I like that you've become
the resident celebration expert for us,
it's like anything celebration
that we have to go to Victor.
- I am taking a bow for you.
- We have one more
category, one more category.
How about the drama.
- Oh the drama.
- Is it on there or no?
- Let's see here.
- I guess not, alright pretend.
Speaking of drama.
- I'm gonna go with what history says
and I think it's gonna
be Antonio Brown on this
and I'm gonna stick with that thought.
I like the way Juju
Smith-Schuster is maturing
into not just a mentor
to those younger players
but an actual leader on the Steelers team.
And for Antonio Brown there
are a lot of personalities
on this roster now.
Obviously, we know Jon Bruden
is the focal point of this
team no matter who's on it.
But I think there's going to
be points during the season
where the AB of Pittsburgh
will show its face in Oakland.
- You cannot tell, we will
not get through this season
without him getting irked with
Derek Carr, there's no way.
- It takes one sailed ball
and he's gonna come at like,
really, really?
- Put some money on it.
- The ESPYS are right around the corner,
who is getting your vote
for the best record-breaking performance.
Come on, you know Drew
Brees wants your vote.
- [Commentator] Drew Brees has done it,
NFL's all time leading passer.
- (crowd cheering drowns out
speaker) an award for right?
- Remember that degree
you got in taxation?
Of course you don't because you didn't.
Your job isn't understanding tax code,
it's understanding why that
will get him a body like that.
Move. That.
Your job isn't doing hard work.
Here, it's making her do hard work
and getting paid for it.
- [Narrator] Snap and sort your expenses
to save over 4600 of tax time.
- Jody, it's time to get yours.
- [Narrator] QuickBooks, backing you.
- This is owed to State Farm for winning
five JD Power awards in
a row for life insurance.
(playing flute)
In B minor.
- [Narrator] Great stuff.
- Not running.
Why am I not running?
Because the new DQ sour Blizzard menu
is only here for a few more
weeks with seven great flavors
like new sour patch
kids and Brownie dough.
- Not running.
- [Narrator] DQ, happy tastes good.
- [Narrator] The hamsters
run hopelessly in their cage,
content on their endless quest to nowhere.
(engine roaring)
But perhaps this year, a more
exhilarating endeavor awaits.
(tires screeching)
Defy the laws of human nature
at the Summer Audi sales event.
Get exceptional offers now.
- So I can buy from Enterprise Car Sales
and you'll take any trade in?
- That's right.
- Great! There you go.
- Well it does need to be a vehicle.
- But I need this out of my house.
- [Narrator] With a fair transparent value
for every trade-in
Enterprise makes it easy.
(grill sizzling)
(music)
- [Narrator] Tegate, bold on the outside,
light on the inside.
- [Narrator] You check in frequently
to see how the markets are doing
but what you really need to
know is how you're doing.
Where do you go for that?
Right here.
PersonalCapital.com.
Join for free, you'll get
a dashboard that shows you
all your accounts in one
place, income, spending,
investments, even your net
worth all in real time.
You'll get all these free
retirement and investing tools.
Including a retirement planner
that takes the guesswork
out of retirement, plus
wealth management options.
Join at PersonalCapital.com
- What's good Josh?
It's Deshaun.
Man I know what you're going through,
you know sometimes you get a great hand
and other times you don't.
Living in your dad's
car, always on the move,
you played the hand you
had and it paid off.
And the cards are about
to be dealt again Josh.
- [Announcer] The Oakland
Raiders select Josh Jacobs.
- [Deshaun] This is your time my dog.
- If something happened to
you, what would happen to them?
Their home, their
education, their future ?
You need life insurance and
chances are Select Quote
can help you get it for
less than a $1 a day.
- [Narrator] Select Quote found Jacob, 40,
a $500,000 policy for only $19 a month.
And Select Quote found his wife, Wendy,
a $500,000 policy for only $17 a month.
- Our secret?
At Select Quote we
aggressively comparison shop
up to ten highly rated companies
to find you the company
with the best rates.
- [Narrator] We found Gary,
35, a $1,000,000 policy
for only $22 a month.
- Why pay more?
Give your family the security they need
at a price you can afford.
- [Narrator] Call 1-800-781-6807
or go to SelectQuote.com now
and get the insurance your family needs.
- [Narrator] At a price you can afford.
Select Quote, we shop, you save.
- [Commentator] Drew Brees finds
himself only 35 yards away.
- It's about us, it's about our strength!
- [Commentator] Just Peyton
Manning left to pass,
he starts in shotgun, drops
back, looks to the far sideline.
Wide open and Smith what a way to do it!
- [Commentator] Drew Brees is the NFL's
all time leading passer.
- I won, how about that!?
- [Commentator] There's only one word
that comes to mind, greatness.
- [Wendy] Well we continue to
highlight some of the stars
around the NFL that earned
ESPY nominations this year.
The amazing moment from Drew Brees
is up for the ESPY for best
record breaking performance.
Brees broke the NFL passing record
when he passed Peyton
Manning's mark of 71,940 yards.
And Victor you made this
point yesterday and it's true.
I think last year was his
best bet at winning the MVP
you just had this pesky
little Patrick Mahomes
who did things that just
didn't seem possible
to keep Brees from winning that award.
- Exactly, and then how do you amass
such a monumental record like this
on an illustrious career
that he's had and not win
the league MVP one time.
I mean obviously, probably
Peyton Manning won
a couple of those, Tom Brady,
all of those tremendous players.
But he's gotta get it one time,
I mean he's put numbers up
each and every year.
I think there's years
that he kinda just goes under the radar
out there in New Orleans
with those play makers
and everybody he's got.
I think this is the year where he's like,
you know what I'm gonna put
a nice pretty little red bow
on this career and put a
NFL league MVP under my belt
and get back to the big dance
hopefully and keep things going.
- So, in fairness he has
been a Superbowl MVP,
two time offensive player
- Ten years.
- But the hall of fame quality
quarterback Drew Brees'
you would like to see him go.
Although I know he'd take
another Lombardi Trophy
any day of the week.
- Now that you can't dispute.
But at least give him one
League MVP, he's earned it.
- We'll show you why how about this?
How about the best of
the best of Drew Brees.
- [Victor] This is vintage right here.
- [Wendy] Yeah vintage '04 he was a
(speaks in foreign language).
Play action, deep to Erick Parker,
breaks a tackle for a 79 yard touchdown.
- [Victor] I like it,
showing that arm off.
- [Wendy] In black and white there.
- [Victor] Real early, real
pixelated, grainy, I love it.
- [Mike] Pixelated or something like that.
- [Wendy] 2004 against the Packers.
Three steps up, just
glazed this one perfectly
into the arms of Brandin Cooks,
a 50 yard touchdown strike.
- [Mike] You know what else is crazy?
- [Wendy] That is a dime.
- [Mike] He's stepping up in the pocket.
A lot of times you see
younger quarterbacks
step up in the pocket
and just check it out.
He's stepping up in the
pocket and keeping his eyes
down the field put so much
pressure on a defense.
- [Wendy] '06 against the Bengals.
The handoff here it's a flee flicker
and then Joe Horn there
between two defenders,
a 72 yard touchdown and
it's that kind of arm
that we see on occasion.
And that's Victor Cruz ass right there.
On moving now to the modern
day against the Panthers,
Brees here to Ted Ginn
in the end zone 49 yards.
- [Victor] The consistency
that we're seeing here
is he's not even being touched,
there are barely even people around him
while he's making these throws.
Like that's indicative to the
type of team he's been around
that offensive line
taking good care of him.
- [Wendy] '06 NFC
Championship, Saints and Bears.
Brees here to Reggie Bush.
- [Mike] You know that's a great example
of a really effective quarterback play.
Sometimes you have to
throw as hard as you can.
That was a great touch throw.
It led the running back
who takes it all the way
by what touch he has.
And that's an underrated
aspect of playing quarterback.
- [Wendy] Then 2016 against the Raiders.
The longest career pass, a 90...
Is this a 98?
Well he's got the...
Little yards out to catch
- [Victor] One yard back.
- [Wendy] To Brandin Cooks.
An incredible career,
certainly should be featured
on the hall of fame.
Perhaps a future NFL MVP,
you can vote in the ESPYS
right now at ESPYS.com.
Again, Brees up for record
breaking performance
along with three other moments
including Klay Thompson's record
for three pointers in a game with 14.
Alright, we gave you our opinion
but who are you crowning
the NFL Highlight King?
Is it Mahomes, Sequon,
Kyler, Dennis Green?
Let us know what's happening next.
- Now, if you wanna crown
'em, then crown their (beep),
but they are who we thought they were.
- What's up Marquise this Juice,
listen, it's not about
height, it's about heart.
It breaks through walls
and outruns demons.
It outworks everybody.
When they see that,
they ain't gonna know what to do with you.
- [Announcer] The Baltimore
Ravens select Marquise Brown.
- Bless up my boy.
♪ Take your time ♪
♪ Build a home ♪
♪ Build a place where we all can belong ♪
- [Narrator] Give extra, get extra.
With new Extra Refreshers gum.
(mountain yodeling)
(rope whirring)
(fireworks popping)
- Look, make a wish.
- I wish for a Biggie Bag from Wendy's.
- I wish everyone loved
each other and was--
- That is a great wish Jimmy.
- [Narrator] Get a Bacon Double
Stack with a quarter pound
of fresh beef, nuggets, fries and a drink
for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
(helicopter engine rumbling)
- Thanks for the ride along, Captain,
I've never been in one of
these before even on GEICO's.
Oh, oh, oh, here we go, here we go.
- You got cut off there,
what were you saying?
Maybe the GEICO's have
been proudly serving
the military for over 75 years,
is that what you wanted to say?
I have to say, you seem
a lot chatty around TV.
- [Narrator] GEICO, proudly
serving the military
for over 75 years.
- You okay back there buddy?
- [Woman] Thanks Golden Corral,
Dan gets a slow smoked
sirloin and my little trio
are as happy as shrimp, oops, clams.
And mom, got it all,
hook line and sirloin.
The slowest smoked
sirloin and shrimp trio.
Golden Corral, the only one for everyone.
- [Announcer] How do you
gage the greatness of an SUV.
Is it to carry cargo?
Or to carry on a legacy?
Is it its design of strength,
or its sign of intelligence?
In crossing harsh terrain
or breaking new ground?
This is the time to get
an exceptional offer
on the Mercedes of your mid-summer dreams
at the Mercedes-Benz Summer Event.
Going on now.
Lease the GLA 250 SUV
for just $329 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz Summer Event.
Mercedes-Benz, the best or nothing.
- [Narrator] Discover a
new wave of refreshment
crafted using our unique and pure process.
White Claw Hard Seltzer.
Nothing tastes quite like it.
- Bro.
- [*Man] (gasps) I got this!
- Bro!
- Bros?
(bell dings)
- Bro.
(gentle music)
- [All] Bro!
- Bro?
- Bro.
- Oh, bro.
- [All] Oh!
(all moaning)
- Later bromies.
- Bros.
- Bro!
- [Narrator] Stuber in theaters July 12th.
- [Announcer] NFL Live is
brought to you by GEICO,
15 minutes could save you
15% or more on car insurance.
- [Wendy] Canadian football
league action Thursday on ESPN,
it's the 3-0 Hamilton Tiger-Cats
take on the Montreal
Alouettes at 7:30 Eastern.
To get ESPN Plus, download the ESPN app
or visit us at espnplus.com.
And do not forget Sports
Center at 6:00 Eastern.
After the Getup NBA Free Agency Special
with Kevin Negandhi and Michelle Eaves.
They'll have the latest on
Kawhi's deciding factors.
Plus reaction and analysis
from the US Women,
their semi-final against
England and of course
day two at Wimbledon.
Sports Center 6:00 Eastern
on ESPN and the ESPN app.
Everybody stated their case,
it's not a real ESPY but
we're handing one out.
The NFL Highlight King and Dianna Russini
who made the case for Patrick Mahomes.
I don't know guys, I happen to agree.
I mean the man is a highlight machine.
- [Mike] I'll throw a challenge flag here,
we're talking about the NFL right?
We haven't had any NFL
players yet for Tyler
so we're in the wrong category.
We got the right player
maybe in the wrong category.
- So what you're saying
you were handicapped
from the get go?
- (crosstalk drowns out speaker)
- So put the pressure on you then.
So, are you going with team
Victor with Sequon Barkley
or team Diana Russini
with Patrick Mahomes?
- I'm a free agent, I'm going
with the highest bidder.
- Okay we'll see how it works.
- We'll talk offscreen.
- Listen, July 4th holiday,
we wanna say a special thank you
to all our men and women
serving around the world.
We appreciate.