- [Reporter] July 4th, this is not out
of the realm that has happened before.
- Yeah, it is not that unusual.
We've just seen such
an acceleration, right,
and the way free agency works overall.
We've never seen this much money
committed in the first 24 hours.
- No, it's over almost four billion.
- Right, and there you go.
So we're on day four, calm down,
be zen, do what you need to do.
We will get you through
the Kawhilight Zone
because we're back later
tonight, at 7:00 eastern.
Come right back, we'll
be here waiting for you.
(upbeat music)
- Straight ahead on Daily Wager,
the dog days of summer are here.
How a holiday heat wave could affect
baseball totals across the next few days
and could that sunshine
also affect hotdogs?
The voice of the Nathan's
Hotdog Eating Contest,
joins us to tell you how to
bet the contest, tomorrow.
Plus, we head to Indianapolis
for more football prop bets.
Can Andrew Luck and T.Y. Hilton
take Indy back to the playoffs?
Happy hump day, welcome into Daily Wager.
I am Doug Kezirian, and
we'd also like to welcome
those watching on ESPN2, today.
In case you have never seen
the show, over the next hour,
we hope to make you a more
informed sports bettor.
We have a packed show
coming up and who knows,
Kawhi could maybe make a decision
at any second and that would obviously,
turn the NBA future odds upside down.
Until then, let's get rolling
with the rest of the show,
which includes the Subway Series.
First pitch, about an hour away.
Mets beat the Yanks last night,
just New York Yankees second
loss in their last 15 games.
Also, the home run record's been snapped.
Tonight, Domingo German makes
his first start since June 7th.
He had an ERA over 8 1/2 in his last
three starts, before a hip injury.
Jason Vargas, Vargas,
he's 2.36 ERA in his last seven starts.
Despite those trends, the
Bombers are favored for the game
in the first five and
the run total is 10, 10!
Joe Fortenbaugh joins me
from the Bay Area, here.
Joe, what's your play in this one?
- Doug, it may sound crazy but I like
the Mets at plus 130, in this matchup.
The Yanks scored just two runs
in that game, last
night, against the Mets.
That was just the third
time in their last 39 games
that they scored two or fewer runs.
Now, a lot of that is due
credit to Zack Wheeler,
in the Met bullpen, which
showed up last night
but I gotta wonder, after
that series across the pond
against the Red Sox, maybe
there's a little jet lag
and fatigue at play here, for the Yankees,
so I'm gonna keep that in mind.
As you mentioned, it's the lefty,
Jason Vargas, pitching
for the Mets tonight.
Two or fewer earned runs in
10 of 13 starts this year.
The Mets are six and two in
his last eight home starts
and not only that, the Yanks are just 24th
in OPS against left-handed pitching
and will be without Edwin
Encarnacion tonight.
So you add it all up, I like
the Mets here at plus 130.
- All right, sounds good
and just to give you
a little push back, Joe, I've
heard the whole jet lag thing
but the Boston Red Sox did put up 10 runs
last night or maybe the Blue Jays
were just that bad
yesterday, we shall see.
So, you're on the Mets.
I know I talked you into the first
five yesterday, my apologies.
Yanks, Mets, though just
one of five games tonight
with a total of at least 10 runs.
Astros, Rockies, leading the
way with a total of 14 1/2.
They combine for 17 last
night, at Coors Field.
Let's go out to Las Vegas.
Preston Johnson joins me
from Planet Hollywood,
overlooking Caesers.
Preston, what do your
numbers have an edge on,
in terms of all those high over/unders?
- It's the Astros, Rockies under 14 1/2.
My projection is 13.1
runs and that accounts
for nine mile per hour
winds to dead center.
It accounts for the fact,
they're obviously playing at Coors Field,
and we even talked about yesterday,
it's crazy having these Astros bats,
which are so much better than the Rockies,
hitting in Coors Field, and I still,
looking at this number, think
this is way too drastic,
and you look at the pitching
match of Wade Miley.
I mean this guy's been
just stellar for two years
and if you say, oh, someone
from the American League
pitching in Coors for the first time,
he was with the Diamondbacks,
he's accustomed to pitching in Coors.
He even pitched there last year,
when he was at the Brewers.
So he has some reps there at Coors Field.
I don't think that's gonna mess him up.
He's 75th percentile, league
wide and hard hit percentage.
Waited on base against, expected
batting average against,
all of these metrics
and on the other side,
Lambert, I mean he's a rookie.
He hasn't been pitching too well
but he's the number one
prospect for the Rockies.
That is the concern some, is
that the Astros just go nuts.
But 14, that's way to drastic.
I have it right at 13
almost, I gotta go under.
- All right, and on those
lists of double digit totals,
if I had to pick one, I'd go over 11 1/2
with the Phillies and Braves.
Both pitchers have really struggled.
Bryse Wilson, ERA over
eight, Nick Pivetta,
at ERA over seven in
his last three starts.
I know it's an umpire
that would favor pitchers
instead of batters here, but
I'm not gonna overthink it.
I'll take the over, in that one.
Preston, sit tight for that.
And Joe, what about you on
that list of over/unders,
the double digits, which
one jumps out to you?
- The second half of the White
Sox, Tigers, doubleheader.
I'm going under 10 1/2 runs,
due largely to the unknown
variety of pitchers that
we're seeing tonight.
For the Tigers, it's going
to be Tyler Alexander,
the rookie southpaw.
Opponents hit just 234 against
him in the month of June.
There's virtually no tape on the kid,
no experience that the White
Sox will have against him.
So perhaps, the second
half of the doubleheader,
they're tired, they've been
out on the diamond all day.
This kid will be able to take advantage
of them a little bit and not only that,
Chicago's about middle of the pack
in OPS, against left-handed pitching.
Now, on the other side of the equation,
it's gonna be Ross
Detwiler, who just earned
his first Major League Baseball
victory in nearly three years.
His first time out, just a week ago,
went up against Minnesota,
looked really sharp,
gave up just two earned runs
in five innings pitched.
He'll go up against the
Tiger lineup tonight.
That's 25th in OPS, against
left-handed pitching.
So, I think the pitchers
have a little bit of success.
We play the under, in 10
1/2 runs, White Sox, Tigers.
- All right, sounds good.
Sit tight, Joe, much more from both you
and Preston throughout the show.
And we've talked college
football in recent shows,
Big Ten yesterday, also covered the SEC.
Let's do a little ACC.
Here's a look at your highest,
six highest win totals,
courtesy of Caesars,
for the coming season.
No surprise, Clemson with a sizeable gap
over the rest of the conference,
11 1/2 minus 110, either side.
Obviously, Trevor Lawrence returns
for the defending national champions.
Miami at 8 1/2, Virginia Tech at eight,
and a trio of NC State,
Syracuse, and Virginia,
all at 7 1/2, with varying juices on that.
Let's welcome in The Bear, Chris
Fallica and Stanford Steve.
I knew you guys were close if
I mentioned college football.
- Absolutely, let's get it going.
- You ready to fire away?
I'm gonna start with the
defending champs, Clemson, 11 1/2.
- Under.
- Over, look this is FPI,
our Football Power Index
projects them to win all
their games by at least 20,
except for two, home to A&M, and that's 15
and then at South Carolina, 18.
So, all of them by at
least two touchdowns.
Their only questionable games are at home
or just not, it should be wire to wire.
I think Alabama being in the race.
They're gonna hear a lot about that.
We'll keep them on point
and we tend to think,
oh, Clemson always will drop one.
Well, they didn't last year
so we can't assume that,
and I think over 11 1/2.
- Last four years of regular
season, they've lost twice.
Both of them have been,
is 19, 20 point favorites.
- And this is offense.
- The whole Clemsoning thing,
oh, I gotta, that's long gone.
Their offense is great.
The only thing that I,
I would play the over on that, as well.
The only thing I think that
could trip them up is an injury,
which nobody wants to see,
but they're just so much
better than everybody
on the schedule.
- The schedule's been
they get A&M at home,
that's key, obviously.
- Yep.
- The schedule's really favorable
for them to run the table.
- I think what makes it favorable,
we're gonna get to it with
our teams, also though,
but I think the conference is terrible.
- Brutal.
- It is awful.
- Fire away.
- All right, I'll start,
but on the other side,
I look at Florida State, okay.
Now, they were a disaster last year, okay.
- Yes.
- They won five games.
They started nine different combinations
on the offensive line, okay.
Quarterbacks were coming
in and out of there.
Defensively, they were awful.
They didn't rank in the top 100
in any defensive categories.
- They were on the field,
short fields every,
off from the ball point.
- On offense,
I think they averaged 260
yards a game, 21 points.
Those weren't good in
any top 100 categories,
but I look at the experience,
I look at the value
of the recruits that they still had.
Those guys were all
playing out of position
because of injuries and what have you,
and guys just having to have to play
to fill the rosters.
- There was disarray
through the coaching team.
- They're so,
yeah, absolutely.
- There's a lot of reasons.
- But with the combination
of the roster, okay,
and then the schedule,
okay, I think it's doable.
The number is seven, they
have the talent to do it.
When you look at the
schedule, five of the teams
won nine games last year
but that's a big drop off.
Those teams lost a lot of
games and I think it's pretty
favorable when you look at everything.
I take three games that aren't winnable,
at Clemson, at Florida, at Virginia.
- We talked last week,
about those week one lies,
when they came out and
Boise State, Florida State,
was one of the games that
Doug and I talked about.
I think what you're mentioning,
I like Florida State in that game.
You can not go to Virginia with the chance
to potentially be wanting
to, right off the bat,
offer the year that you had
last year, but you're right.
You think Kendal Briles, maybe
biggest coordinator hire,
going into the 2008, maybe him,
or maybe Alex Grinch at Oklahoma.
- Yeah, I mean, what he has
to play with, Blackman--
- Terry.
- Experienced two years ago.
Terry's a A1 receiver.
- Willie Taggart can recruit.
He's demonstrated that--
- Absolutely.
- In the state of Florida and
he finally gets another year
under his belt to
implement all those guys.
- And I will ask the question,
who do you think is gonna come in?
Not who's gonna play Clemson
in an ACC title game.
Who's the second best
team, when you look at it?
Three months ago, you asked the question
when we did a Kentucky
Derby podcast and I'm like,
I don't know, Syracuse,
they looked great last year.
- FPI says 8.1 win, so they side with you.
Bear, what--
- Early lean.
- Early lean, okay.
What about you, Bear?
- Last year, Steve and I were,
Bullet Shawn B, see we
love Addazio's dudes.
- Love them.
- We went over the six and they cashed.
Problem this year at BC,
Addazio's dudes are gone.
The offensive line is gone.
Ray, Strahan, all those
guys in defense, gone.
I'm on the under this year with BC.
I just look, I think as AJ Dillon went,
and then the injury to quarterback,
the Eagles offense went.
I just don't know if you can
line up an offensive line
and just run Dillon 35
times like they want to.
They got a coordinator
change on both sides
of the ball so we'll see how that goes.
But Addazio, they've been a six
or a seven win every year, under him.
You'll have the Virginia Tech game
to start the year, will be tough.
They should win the next three.
I'm high on Wake Forest, I think the Deacs
are gonna be really good but
look at the way they finish.
I mean, those final five games,
if they haven't gotten
to seven by the time
they go to Clemson, I don't
think they're gonna get it.
- Goodnight, yeah, exactly.
I mean, look at the difference.
That's a Florida State team
and a Boston College team.
Look at the difference in the schedules.
That's why I like
Florida State, it's over,
and you're like, BC's under.
- And why a team like Florida State,
you can be so high on and
then exceeding the number.
They recruit so well, they reload.
It's not like BC has been
recruiting these great, great.
- No, limited.
- They develop players, they find guys
who they can get into their system
and they're a young offensive
line and a lot of turnover.
I'm thinking get into a bowl this year
with six wins would be a good job.
- Of all the ACC teams--
- Really good.
- Between Vegas and what
they project, biggest delta,
biggest difference is
BC to the under, 5.1.
- And I think it's like a--
- You got a calculator over there?
- A spreadsheet here.
(laughing)
My computer--
- It's a map, Steve.
He probably did take it at Stanford.
- I still will say, Virginia and I
have a thing, they look good.
- Yeah, all right, well fortunately,
- We've broke up like that.
- We have plenty of time.
We got game one lines, or
week one lines we can dissect,
as well, throughout
the rest of the summer.
Bear and Stanford Steve
here, in the house.
We all like a little tennis action,
especially in the morning, right,
not a lot on, fire away on.
- Give me that money!
- Brad Gilbert
as we think about Wimbledon
underdogs, galore.
We'll have Patrick McEnroe
next, with some picks.
Also, props for Colts
players, courtesy of Caesars.
Where do you stand on Andrew Luck
passing touchdowns this year, 32 1/2.
We'll break it down as
Daily Wager rolls on.
(upbeat music)
- [Woman] What makes
DiGiorno Crispy Pan Pizza
different than delivery?
♪ Pan, pan, pan, pan ♪
- [Man] You bake it fresh in its own pan
giving our DiGiorno pizza
a crispy caramelized crust.
It's not delivery, it's DiGiorno.
- [Advertiser] Why use
Post-it Extreme Notes?
Because they make your message stick,
getting it said and done
right the first time.
- [Homeowner] Oh, come on!
- [Advertiser] Stop the re-work
with Post-it Extreme Notes.
- Not running, why am I not running?
Because the DQ Summer
Blizzard Menu is only here
for a few more weeks
with seven great flavors
like new Sour Patch
Kids and Brownie Dough.
- Not running.
- [Woman] DQ, Happy Tastes Good.
♪ I'm tasting olives ♪
♪ Roasted pine nuts ♪
♪ Mmm, this red pepper ♪
♪ That's spicy stuff ♪
- [Man] Fresh flavor, feel
good food, Sabra Hummus.
♪ I just had Sabra Hummus ♪
♪ And now, I feel good ♪
- So I can buy from Enterprise Car Sales
and you'll take any trade-in?
- That's right.
- Great!
There you go.
- Well, it does need to be a vehicle.
- But I need this out of my house.
- [Woman] With fair transparent
value for every trade-in,
Enterprise makes it easy.
(food sizzling)
(hip hop music)
(singing in foreign language)
- [Man] Tecate, bold on the
outside, light on the inside.
- [Cameraman] Going on five.
- Hi!
- Oh, we all just got new
smartphones at Cricket!
- Hi!
- Hola!
- Okay, Bye!
- Bye!
- [Woman] Thanks Golden Corral.
Dan gets his slow-smoked
sirloin and my little trio
are as happy as shrimp, oops, clams,
and Mom, got it all,
hook, line, and sirloin.
The slow-smoked sirloin and shrimp trio,
Golden Corral, the only one for everyone.
(dogs barking)
- What about him?
♪ I know ♪
- Let's do it.
♪ These winding roads ♪
♪ Will lead me home ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ I'll go ♪
- Come on!
- [Advertiser] This summer,
add a new member to the family.
Hurry into the Mercedes-Benz Summer Event,
today, for exceptional offers.
Lease the GLC 300 SUV
for just $419 a month
through Mercedes-Benz
Summer Event, going on now.
(upbeat music)
♪ Jump if they want it ♪
(yells musically)
♪ They can come and get it ♪
- [Man] Break down every
dinger with launch angle,
exit velocity, apex, and distance.
The T-Mobile Home Run
Derby Statcast Edition,
powered by AWS, Monday at eight on ESPN2.
- [Doug] Back with you on Daily Wager.
Today at Wimbledon, recapping
just some of the action.
But hey, the biggest story
probably is Coco Gauff,
the 15 year old American, what a story.
She won today as a plus 155 underdog,
a pick that Brad Gilbert gave
out yesterday on this show.
So, she moves on to the third round,
she'll face Polona Hercog.
So we gave that one out
yesterday, as a winner.
What about what else is going on?
Lots of upsets so far but
the big names do remain
and are in action tomorrow
in the second round.
Roger Federer, minus 20,000 favorite
against Britain's Jay Clarke.
Fed was minus 15,000 in the first round.
Rafael Nadal, looking for a
second straight Grand Slam win,
not nearly as big of a favorite, minus 360
against Australia, Nick Kyrgios.
Those players have split
six career meetings.
Kyrgios did win the last,
and on the women's side,
11th seed, Serena Williams
is going to face a qualifier.
She's a perfect 18 and O
in second round matches
in the All England Club and
is a minus 750 favorite.
So let's take a look at some
of the other notable matchups
as we, that catch our eye,
Angelique Kerber, minus 950.
Hey, you don't like the big juice,
you don't wanna lay the lumber,
you could always do a money line parlay,
and Sam Querrey with the upset,
is now minus 460 in his second match.
As for the couple of potential
upsets in other picks,
let's turn it over to our Patrick McEnroe.
- Expecting more beautiful
weather on day four at Wimbledon
and the match we've all been
waiting for on the men's side
in round two will be
between the two-time champ,
Rafael Nadal and the
wacky one from Australia,
Nick Kyrgios, who can also play
some serious tennis,
particularly on grass.
Remember a couple of years
ago, Kyrgios upset Nadal,
right here at Wimbledon on center court.
I'm not expecting that to happen tomorrow.
I think Nadal's ready for this,
having won his 12th French
Open, he's got some confidence.
Of course, this is his
least favorite surface.
The favorite surface for Kyrgios,
but he does not look like the player
he was a couple of years ago.
I expected Nadal to maybe drop a set,
but probably win this one in four sets.
On the ladies side, Sloane Stephens,
she's a number nine seed here.
She'll try to celebrate the Fourth of July
with a second round win, taking
on Wang Yafan from China,
who's a solid player, ranked
in the high 50s in the world.
But I think Stephens,
despite playing on a surface
which hasn't been her best over the years,
she looked good in round number one.
I expect her to win
comfortably in straight sets.
Back to you, Doug.
- All right, Patrick,
thanks so much and look,
it's Independence Day and
fire away in the morning,
throughout the afternoon,
and you got some baseball
on July 4th, but that is the
best part about Wimbledon.
The women's soccer we've talked about,
action throughout the day.
You can fire away on
more than 10 1/2 hours
of second round play, ESPN, ESPN+,
and always streaming live on the ESPN app.
And we've been talking a
lot of pro football props,
doing tours of each division.
We're doing the South Divisions this week.
AFC South, here with
the Colts player props,
courtesy of Caesars.
Andrew Luck's passing
touchdown total, 32 1/2.
He's gone over just twice
in his five full seasons.
Marlon Mack needs a
1,000 yard rushing season
to go over his total.
The Colts have had one, 1,000 yard rush
in the last decade, that
was Frank Gore in 2016.
Let's bring in now, our male modelers,
Preston Johnson and Mike
Clay, who have spreadsheets
and laptops in hand,
as we break this down.
Andrew Luck, 32 TD passes.
We'll start with you, Mike.
What do your numbers say here?
- Definitely going over on this one.
This guy is 39 passing
touchdowns last season.
That was second most in
the NFL, behind only,
some guy named Patrick Mahomes,
you may have heard of him.
The last time we saw Andrew
Luck for a full 16 game season,
he had 40 passing touchdowns and really,
the key here is opportunity.
You have a stat, OTD,
which looks at essentially,
expected passing touchdowns
based on your opportunity,
where you are on the field,
your volume of throws.
Luck, last year, topped
in the NFL at 34.0.
The key, throws them to the end zone.
The Colts had 50 last season.
That was most in the league.
This offense sets up for him
to throw a ton of touchdowns.
- All right, sounds good.
Preston, what do your projections have?
- You guys know, we do this
every day and I'm generally,
pretty married to my projections
and I had Andrew Luck
come in at 28 touchdowns
and I couldn't believe it,
and there's no way I'm
betting under on this, though.
You look at it and I agree with Mike.
There's so much value
here with Andrew Luck,
assuming he plays a full season.
I'm not sure how he
doesn't go over 32 1/2.
So I actually, am staying off of this,
despite my projections pointing
to an edge, on the under,
but because I am lower on
Andrew Luck's projections,
there are some correlated bets
which we'll get to here in a bit,
which I think are safer and better,
as far as some of these receivers go.
- I like that gut check and especially
with the offensive line improving
over the last couple of seasons.
His health is more likely,
obviously, to stay intact.
T.Y. Hilton, receiving yards, 1,210 1/2.
Mike, we'll start with
you, what do you got?
- Well, I'm going over
on this one, for sure.
I mean, you look back at
the last three seasons
that T.Y. Hilton and Andrew Luck
have played together in full.
Hilton has blown this nuffer
away all three seasons
and there's a few things in play here.
One of them is durability.
He's missed four games in
seven seasons, in the league.
He's finished top 17 in receiving yards
each of the past six seasons and guys,
he's been in the 80th percentile or better
in yards per reception, each
of the past five seasons.
It's Andrew Luck's go-to guy.
This is a high volume, pass heavy offense.
Hilton, I think, gets
to this number easily.
- All right, Preston, and you?
- This is one where we disagree.
So I'm correlated here
with not really loving
Andrew Luck's numbers
but Hilton, I have at 1,140 yards.
So for me, there is a
slight edge to the under.
Then you actually just look at the scope
of who Luck will be throwing to.
They went out of their way
to bring in Devin Funchess.
They drafted Parris Campbell
in the second round,
out of Ohio State, who I
think's gonna be stellar.
Then you have Eric Ebron, who played
a bunch last year in tight end.
Well, they have a second
tight end named Jack Doyle,
who missed a lot of last season.
He'll be an option, as well.
I have those two tight ends combined,
projected for over 140 targets.
So for me, I think T.Y. Hilton's
total target share is going down.
I have him under 1,200 yards.
So I like it at 1,210 1/2,
it's a bet under for me.
- All right, so you guys disagree there.
I like that, I like
that you would disagree.
Mike, let's go to you, Marlon Mack,
will he be a 1,000 yard rusher again?
Not combined, just rushing yards.
- Yes, he will and he
sort of was last year,
if you look at his 14 games
including the playoffs.
He had a little over
1,100 yards and again,
that was with playing a situational roll,
for a lot of the early part of the season.
The guy has been terrific
since he's entered the league,
and 4.8 yards per carry, last season.
You don't wanna get too
wrapped up in yards per carry
but he's been above averaging yards
after contact per attempt
in both of his NFL seasons.
He's got a lot of help before contact,
last season, from Quenton Nelson, as well.
And here's the big one,
we know volume is king for running backs.
In his last five games, last season,
he handled at least 75% of the Colts
designed runs in each of those games.
The guy is working his way into becoming
a two-down workhorse
for this Colt's offense.
I like the over, a lot here.
- All right, so Mike, you're certainly
bullish on the Colts offense.
Preston, you mentioned Eric
Ebron just a moment ago,
6 1/2 touchdowns for his prop.
Where are you headed with this?
- This is another gut check
but I'm going with it.
I have projected 5.2 touchdowns.
I mentioned that Jack Doyle is back.
He should be healthier and
I project him to have a good
portion as a second tight end,
of his potential target share.
I think Devin Funchess, I
mean, this guy is 6'4", 240,
as far as red zone opportunities go
and goal line opportunities,
Funchess, Doyle, and Ebron.
Ebron, outside of last year,
where he scored 13 touchdowns,
this is why it's a gut check, under 6 1/2,
he never got more than five
touchdowns in a season.
That was in Detroit, and
Matthew Stafford's not inept.
So for me, I just think there's
so much going around here
now, for Luck, he has so many weapons.
I gotta go under Ebron.
I don't think we'll see
what we did last year.
- And again, a little technicality,
it's total touchdowns.
So it includes a, maybe an inside handoff,
a recovered fumble in the goal
line, something like that,
so it's total touchdown.
- There you go.
That changes everything.
- Yeah, I know.
Yeah, you wanna go back
to your spreadsheet and reevaluate it.
Mike, thank you very much.
More to come from Preston, straight ahead.
And from player props to team
props, Indy's win total is 10,
which is what they won last year.
The over, plus 110 and the
yes, no, to make the playoffs.
Yes, is minus $1.75, which
they sure in fact did
in Frank Reich's first
season with the Colts.
Let's go out to New York and
bring in our Anita Marks.
Anita, over/under 10, now, I am passing
'cause I think it's gonna be right there.
They have to face the NFC
South, really tough schedule,
supposed to be competitive division,
so I think it's gonna
be right around there.
So I'm gonna pass, what about you?
- I'm on the over, a little bit.
I'm not banking the mortgage
on the over but I am putting
a little money on the over
for a number of reasons.
Let's talk about the schedule.
Let's take a look at
the schedule, actually.
I have them winning their
division, the AFC South.
I think they split with Houston.
I think they go two and
O against Tennessee.
They could possibly go two
and O against the Jaguars.
So I'm looking at five and one,
four and three in their division,
easy games, with all due respect
to Oakland, Denver, and Miami.
Here's where it gets tough.
Look at their road games,
and the quarterbacks they're
gonna be facing, you ready?
The Chargers, the Chiefs,
the Steelers, the Texans,
the Saints, it's a tough road game.
I have them going three
and two on the road.
So it's gonna be close
but I think this team
is just so good, Doug, that
I have them at 10, 11 win.
So I'm putting a little money on the over.
- All right, sounds good, that's fair.
I was definitely leaning
that way but I'm gonna pass.
Now, as for the yes, no, I like the yes,
to make the playoffs at minus $1.75.
A little different here than the division
because you could get to the playoffs
and not get over 10 wins, nine or 10 wins
in this division could win it.
So I'm gonna say, I like the yes,
to make the playoffs at minus $1.75.
Obviously, you have the
bonus of the wild card
but that's why I'm
differentiating between that
and over 10 wins, what about you?
- Again, I have them
winning this division.
I love this team, out of all
the 22 starters of course,
on offense and defense,
they only have one guy
not coming back, that's amazing.
That just doesn't happen in
this day and age in free agency.
On top of that, they are one
of the most balanced teams
in the NFL, first and third
down conversions in 2018.
Andrew Luck, when he's healthy,
he's a top five quarterback.
He's got the best
offensive line coming in,
wide receivers, you've
gotta love T.Y. Hilton.
They add Devin Funchess, he's gonna be
a stud in the red zone.
They draft Parris Campbell,
he's a speedy wide receiver.
I love their one-two punch
with their tight ends.
Eric Ebron took a big
step with them this year
as opposed to what we saw in Detroit.
Jack Doyle, he's gonna be
healthy and then they add
Justin Houston on the
defensive side of the ball,
so, I just, I love this team.
I think they're gonna make the playoffs.
I think they win the division, Doug.
- Sounds like we're all
very positive on the Colts.
That's Anita Marks and she'll
join us later in the show
to discuss the weekends PGA tournament.
That's coming up later.
- There you go.
- [Doug] And we're approaching
the bottom of the hour
and in these parts, that means one thing,
Best Bets, just around
the corner, stay tuned.
(upbeat music)
- [Advertiser] New for
summer, here for summer,
arriving this summer,
it's Bud Light Lemon Tea,
new for summer, new for summer.
♪ How can I find a way without ♪
♪ Your Mexican spice ♪
- [Man] You've heard the phenomenon.
Now, experience Nacho fries,
live from your house
with Taco Bell delivery.
- I'm Tom from Kane 11 and
I have one question for you.
What size socks do you wear?
If you're like everyone else we've asked,
just simply don't know, how could you.
All sock companies make their
socks in one size fits all
or just a couple of sizes
to fit every size foot.
At Kane 11, we make our socks
to fit 11 individual sizes,
from seven to 17, that's
right, seven to 17.
No more heel hiking, toe bunching,
or that towel under your toe feeling.
Kane 11 has great colors and looks
to fit everyone's lifestyle,
from crews to athletics,
even our perfectly designed no-shows.
Your feet hold up your whole body,
and the better your socks fit,
the more comfortable
you're gonna feel all day.
That's the Kane 11 promise.
So, stop compromising your comfort.
Try a pair of Kane 11
socks, you'll never go back
to hit or miss size ranges again.
See why Esquire, Men's Health
and Golf Digest are all raving about us.
Go to kane11.com, get
20% off your first order,
only available at kane11.com.
♪ Walk the world with me ♪
- I'm Tracy Morgan and
I'm also the 2019 ESPYS,
where Alex Morgan is up
for best female athlete.
She's actually my first
cousin on my pop's side.
Us Morgs are known for having
calf muscles, go ahead cuzzo.
(upbeat music)
I'm Tracy Morgan and
I'm also the 2019 ESPYS.
Everyone calls Kawhi the silent assassin.
I gave him my number and
the guy won't shut up.
I'm not going maple tree-tapping with you.
Stop calling me Kawhi.
(upbeat music)
- Tell him we're flexible.
- Don't worry, my Dutch is okay.
- Just okay?
- Mm-hmm, this man
(speaking in foreign language)
- Tell him we need this merger.
(speaks in foreign language)
- It's happening.
- Just okay is not okay,
especially when it comes to your network.
AT&T is America's best wireless network
according to America's biggest test.
Now with 5G Evolution,
the first step to 5G,
more for your thing, that's our thing.
- This is our moment, let's get it.
Three, two, one, here we go Peloton.
♪ Ain't my fault ♪
♪ That I'm out here getting loose ♪
♪ Gotta blame it on ♪
- Let's do this together Peloton.
- [Advertiser] One subscription
for the whole family.
Just one part of the best cardio machine
on the planet, Peloton.
- [Man] Not sure you have
the right credit card,
know which one to get?
Turn to the nerds!
Dinner's on me, get it?
(laughs) Oh.
The experts at NerdWallet make it easy
to make smart money moves.
Compare and find the best credit cards
for you at nerdwallet.com
- All right, back with
you, recapping, Best Bets.
Strong night for us on the diamond.
Astros got four runs in the seventh,
turned a three run deficit
into a one run victory.
Plus 117 for Preston, there
on the Stros, A's hit for Joe.
My Rays, Dodgers parlay got there,
thanks to five consecutive walks.
Hey, better lucky than good.
All right, so five and
two for the week, we are,
and let's keep the momentum going.
Here at the desk, Stanford Steve here,
standing by for your best bet.
We'll get that in a moment
but let's go back out to Las Vegas.
Preston, what do you
have for your best bet?
You're on the T-box first.
- I'm going to the Summer League.
In the NBA, the Grizzlies minus
2 1/2 against the Cavaliers,
who we fitted on Monday against the Spurs.
We talked about their inexperience,
the only guy getting run
that has any pro experience
is Nas Mutulong, who played
a total of 85 minutes
for the Jazz the last two years.
On the other side, this Memphis team,
there's a roster filled
with a bunch of guys
who played fairly regular minutes
the last two seasons
when Memphis was tanking.
Ivan Rabb, Washburn,
Watanabe, Jevon Carter,
these guys took total, 63 points,
I think, on Monday when they played.
They all rested yesterday.
Now, Carter, worth noting,
actually just got traded
to the Suns, probably won't
play because they can't afford
him to get injured but these
other three guys combined,
with 34 points, they
have so much experience
compared to the Cavs, who are
playing a bunch of rookies.
It doesn't impact the projection too much.
It should be more like minus five.
We're getting two, 2 1/2
out there on the market.
So I'm going with the Grizzlies.
- [Steve] You believe
in rest days in Vegas,
come on, or was that in Salt Lake?
(laughing)
- This one's in Salt Lake.
- [Steve] All right, a
little different, right.
- The altitude.
- [Doug] Yeah, a little different
extracurricular activity,
fewer distractions, I would say.
- [Steve] You would
think, you would think,
never know.
- You never know.
All right, so Preston's playing
to his home court advantage
out there in Las Vegas.
Joe, what do you got for your best bet?
- The San Francisco Giants at plus 120
over the San Diego Padres,
as they look for the sweep tonight.
The Giant bats have
come alive, as of late.
Three straight wins, all of
which featured 10 or more runs.
Now tonight, the Padres,
who ranked 19th in OPS
are gonna face Giant
right-hander, Shaun Anderson.
Anderson has been the most consistent
pitcher for the Giants this season.
A lot of people may think
that's Madison Bumgarner
but Bumgarner's been up and
down through the months.
Anderson's made nine starts, giving up two
or fewer runs in six of those starts.
Go back to June 12th,
he faces Padre lineup,
four hits, two were in runs
in six innings pitched.
He's gonna take the mound for the Giants,
which is the big edge here.
I think he's extremely undervalued
at this point in the season.
For the Padres, it's
gonna be the youngster,
Cal Quantrill, the righty
pitching against San Francisco.
He's coming out of the bullpen
to make his first start
in a few weeks, six starts this season.
He's got an ERA north of five,
18 earned runs in just 31 innings pitched.
So, I like the Giants
to get the sweep tonight
and then they're off tomorrow,
first time off on July 4th since 1941.
Giants plus 120, you can book it.
- All right, and the Giants bats
have been hot a little bit, in San Diego.
So, we got Preston in Vegas,
picking a Summer League game.
- Yeah, Grizzlies, Giants, parlay.
- So Joe, in the Bay
Area, taking the Giants.
Are you going the
tri-state area for yours?
- Absolutely.
- All right, staying true to form here.
- The Mets aren't gonna win the season
series from the almighty Yankees.
- Yes.
- First time since 2013,
that's not gonna happen.
- No sir.
- Lemans back on the
mound for the Yankees,
take the Yankees.
- Vargas throwing well, lately, no.
- Really.
- All right, so you're sticking
to the home team, so to speak, Preston.
I'm going with my team
and where I'm gonna be
this holiday weekend, I'm
going with the Dodgers.
Look, I got lucky last
night, first one to admit it.
- Lucky!
- Beyond lucky.
- I don't wanna hear about you
with bad beats anymore, ever again.
- Walker Buehler, think about this,
an eight start stretch, an
ERA of 1.64, eight starts,
then got touched up the last one.
That was at Coors Field,
let's throw that out.
Throw out Coors Field.
- Throw it out.
- And the Dodgers are hot,
amazing health record.
- Yeah, thanks to five
straight walks with two outs.
- Well, we're gonna need
to cover a run and a half.
- Which has never been done before.
- We're gonna hope to not to
get to the bottom of the ninth.
We need a little breathing room.
- You need a homer then.
- But I don't think that
Buehler's gonna give up much.
I think this one gets away
from the D-backs and who knows.
Locker room demoralized after that?
- All right.
- I'm hoping certainly shaky.
I'll lay the 1 1/2 minus 120.
I couldn't find any obscene money lines
to parlay with the
Dodgers, straight up, so.
All right, we'll just
lay the run and a half
and try to stay hot this week.
Steve's laying the $1.38, as well.
All of us are playing to
our home teams, I love it.
Joe's plus money with the Giants,
and the Grizzlies for Preston,
out there laying tuna.
A lot of scouting for Preston, I love it.
- [Steve] I know, see him Monday.
- Gold Cup Semi-finals tonight,
men's soccer for the Americans
as they face Jamaica.
Remember they met last
Gold Cup Final in 2017,
two, one victory for the Americans.
Three way betting, U.S.
is 190, minus $1.90 to win
in regulation, in the draw,
plus 275 and Jamaica obviously,
a huge underdog with the over/under
at 2 1/2 and the under is minus $1.90.
For more, let's go out to
Nashville, ahead of tonight's game
and bring in ESPN FC
reporter, Jeff Carlisle.
Jeff, appreciate the taking the time.
U.S. favorite, as you very well know,
but let's go back about a
month ago where they lost
a friendly to Jamaica, one-nil.
How does the team tonight compare
to the one that lost that game?
- Well, it's gonna be
a very different team
that takes the field for
the Unites States tonight.
I count at least seven different players,
will be in the starting
lineup, possibly eight,
and those are key players, as well,
key attacking players
when you're talking about
Christian Pulisic, Weston McKennie.
The Ford is either gonna be
Gyasi Zardes or Jozy Altidore.
None of those players play in that game.
Then you've got the guy
providing the shield
in front of the defense, Michael Bradley.
He's gonna be a key player
for the U.S. tonight.
He's gonna have to play
very well, be very mobile,
and so obviously, it's gonna
be a very different team
for the U.S. that takes the field.
Contrast that with Jamaica,
I counted seven players
that took the field in the
quarter final against Panama,
that were also on the field
that night in Washington, D.C.
when they played that
friendly against the U.S.
So, Jamaica's gonna have a few new faces,
the U.S. is gonna have a lot of new faces.
- All right, and the over/under's 2 1/2?
How much scoring do you expect?
- I don't expect a whole
lot of scoring tonight.
Jamaica has only conceded two goals
in the entire tournament.
The United States has kept a clean sheet
in every one of their Gold Cup games.
Their defense has been very stout,
that the back line has
been very consistent.
They've been tested, I mean,
Curacao, in the quarter finals
was definitely a team that
tested the U.S. with possession.
They had some good chances, as well,
and Zack Steffen in goal
has been very, very good.
So, on the other hand,
you've got Andre Blake,
who's a goal keeper that MLS
fans are very familiar with.
He plays for the Philadelphia Union.
He's also been very good and
came up big a couple of times
in the quarter final win over Panama.
So, I don't expect a whole
lot of scoring tonight.
I expect it to be a very tight semifinal
like we saw last night
with Mexico and Haiti.
So again, 2 1/2 goals
seems like a lot to me,
so I expect it to be a
one-nil affair, for sure.
- In favor of who?
- The United States, I would
agree that the United States
are slight favorites, but again,
Jamaica's played them very tough
and Jamaica's gone deep
in this tournament,
the last two additions.
They've made the final two times,
so when it comes to the Gold Cup,
Jamaica's a very difficult
team to break down, so.
But I look at the, I see the
U.S. getting through tonight.
- All right, sounds good.
That's ESPN FC reporter, Jeff Carlisle,
joining us from Nashville,
ahead of tonight's
Gold Cup semifinal, thank you, Jeff.
- You're welcome.
- [Doug] And we're continuing to cover
a wide range of sports.
Coming up next, the number
one golfer in the world,
Brooks Koepka, is your
favorite at the 3M Open
and we'll tell you why
he's not the best bet.
Plus, Joey Chestnut, a heavy favorite
at the Hot Dog Eating Contest
but our expert will tell you
why weather could be a big
factor in the over/under
of hotdogs eating, that's next.
(upbeat music)
- My insurance rates are
probably gonna double.
- But dad, you've got Allstate.
With accident forgiveness,
they guarantee your rates
won't go up just because of an accident.
- Smart kid.
- Indeed.
Are you in good hands?
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Lower carbs, lower calories,
higher expectations, the light beer
you've been waiting for has
arrived, Corona Premier.
(upbeat music)
♪ Summer nights ♪
♪ Keeping me up ♪
♪ I wanna waste time ♪
♪ Just looking at the sky ♪
♪ For the stars ♪
♪ Mind wandering far ♪
♪ Like my 16 ♪
♪ Dreaming in the dark ♪
♪ Love the wind in my hair ♪
♪ As I drive my car ♪
♪ And make me feel free ♪
- [Announcer] Now, get exceptional offers
at the Infiniti Plus Summer Sales Event.
- [Announcer] It's time for
our lowest prices of the season
on the sleep number 360 smart bed.
It senses your movement and automatically
adjusts to keep you both comfortable.
The queen sleep number 360
C4 smart bed, now $1,299
plus free premium delivery when
you add a base, ends Sunday.
- [Woman] Look, make a wish.
- I wish for a Biggie Bag from Wendy's.
- I wish everyone loved
each other and was all--
- That was a great wish, Jimmy.
- [Advertiser] Get a Bacon
Double Stack with a quarter pound
of fresh beef, nuggets, fries,
and a drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Built by
champions and contenders,
built towards the future, on
the foundation of our past,
built to defy expectations
and challenge convention,
built by those who came
before and everyone to come,
get your tickets today to witness
the 2019 U.S. Open, built for glory.
(kids cheering)
- Coach, it's kinda hard to see the ball.
- I've been there.
I had a TV service with
hardly any sports in 4K,
couldn't see any of the quality details.
I switched to DirecTV, now I
get the most live sports in 4K.
- So, how does that help me?
- But really, it doesn't, I
don't know why I told you that.
Go get 'em, sport!
- [Advertiser] Live sports that aren't
in 4K are just kinda TV.
Don't just kinda TV, DirecTV.
Don't have 4K, call 1-855-watch4K
and ask for it today.
- [Announcer] When buying a car,
we know there are a lot of questions.
- What's the mileage?
- How many previous owners?
- Does the dealer have good reviews?
- Does it include a navigation system?
- [Announcer] We all know
the most important question
is always--
- Am I getting a good deal?
- CarGurus has the answer.
Only CarGurus gives every
car a deal rating from great
to overpriced and sorts
the best ones first,
making it fast and easy
to find great deals
from top rated dealers near you.
Find your great deal today at CarGurus.
- Time now, for Daily Diamond Dogs
and the best part is the
dog we get to feature.
This is Baxter, who is a
service dog here at ESPN,
works with our audio engineer, Tyler.
Baxter, as you can see,
certainly in charge
and he's now responsible for hitting
the bleep button whenever
I lose a bet on set.
So Baxter is profiled as we take a look
at the biggest underdogs of the night
and the biggest one is
actually a home team.
The Blue Jays, in Toronto,
facing Chris Sale and the Red Sox.
D-backs above 200 on the comeback face,
and the Dodgers and Walker
Buehler, as I noted earlier,
and the Marlins did close around plus 240
against the Mets, but first
pitch already underway at 6:05.
Joe Fortenbaugh, back with me.
What's your Diamond Dog tonight, Joe?
- All right, Doug, limited options tonight
and there is no way I wanna get
in front of the Walker Buehler train.
So we're gonna fade Chris
Sale and the Red Sox.
Give me Toronto plus 240.
Chris Sale broke from the gate
in sluggish fashion this season.
A lot of people wondering what went wrong,
settled down and was outstanding.
Now, as of late, a bit iffy,
not terrible, but a bit iffy.
Last restarts, he's
given up 10 earned runs
over 17 innings pitched.
Again, not terrible, but
maybe there's something there
we can take advantage
of, in this situation.
One of those starts was at Fenway
against Toronto, gave up a few runs,
didn't exactly work
that deep into the game.
So this may be a spot where
you can take advantage
of Chris Sale, who by the way,
this is the worst hard hit
percentage of his entire career
and his fastball's down
about a full mile an hour,
over his results from last
season, so not the guy
we saw last season, still
a very good pitcher.
Boston has lost five of
eight, so this could be a nice
little opportunity here to
back the dog at plus 240.
- Yeah, I can't fault you there,
given the price there on the dog.
I'm gonna go with The Royals plus 145,
a little bit of a force, we
usually, has to go higher.
In two starts since returning from injury,
Mike Clevinger has allowed 12 runs.
It sure looks like he returned
too quickly from that back injury.
Something just doesn't seem right,
so I'll take the Royals at
home, plus the juice there.
And by the way, if you wanna
send in pics of your dog,
we will profile them every
time we do this segment,
which isn't necessarily every
day, just tweet me @DougESPN.
Joe will be back momentarily,
but one final look
at Baxter, in charge, how awesome!
PGA Tour, heading to Minnesota
for the inaugural 3M
Open at TPC Twin Cities.
No surprise, Brooks Koepka,
your favorite at eight to one.
The only player with single digit odds.
That's followed by Jason Day
and Hideki Matsuyama, 11 to one a piece,
Bryson DeChambeau, at 15 to one.
Not posted here is lefty,
Phil Mickelson at 40 to one.
Let's welcome back Anita Marks here,
to talk a little golf,
given it is a Wednesday.
She appears here on the
show every Wednesday.
Of the favorites, Anita, which
one grabs your attention?
- I'm going with Hideki, quick
note here, 27 water hazards,
74 bunkers, that's what these
guys are gonna be facing.
And Hideki has been coming
in red hot this season.
This is a guy who has
not missed a cut, Doug,
not one all season long.
He's in great form, he's
red hot with his irons
and each and every week,
we talk about the analytics
that's going to play well on this course.
Birdie average, he ranks 10th on tour,
par five scoring, he ranks 25th and also,
strokes gained, tee-to-green,
he ranks fourth on tour,
so he's up there, top 25 in this category.
He's gonna do exceptionally well.
I like him, I'm putting some
hard earned money on him.
- Yeah, you liked him last week,
did well, T-13, finished up there.
What's another golfer
that you think kinda grabs
your attention, in terms of value?
- Let's go to Patrick Reed,
and he's coming in tied
for fifth last week, so he's coming in hot
and he's coming in with
a lot of confidence,
and when you look at what
he's been able to do,
the history in Minnesota.
Let's go back to the 2016 Ryder
Cup where he got that name,
Captain America, because
he took worry to the limit.
His putting is a lot better
and each and every week,
we like to talk about the grass.
It's bent grass this week,
so the greens aren't gonna be
as difficult as some
of these guys have seen
in previous weeks, so I like Patrick Reed.
- All right, sounds good,
can't let you get out of here
without a DFS lineup,
advice, fire away here.
- You got it, as always, the two guys
that I first talk about,
my long, my short odds.
I like to play them in DFS, as well.
So, I'm going with Hideki and Patrick.
Who am I gonna round it
out with, DeChambeau,
fifth in birdie average
and par five scoring.
His putting is finally coming back
and he does extremely well
with generous fairways
and that's what he's gonna
see, starting tomorrow.
Niemann, back to back top fives, why?
He has a new putting practice
that he's been practicing with
and it's really been helping him.
Also, 31st strokes gained tee-to-green.
Homa, this is another guy who
just makes every cut 48th,
par five scoring and here's
the thing, three par fives,
593 yards, 596 yards,
there's some long par fives.
And Redman is coming in red hot as well,
second last week with 19
under, on the tournament.
This is his third PGA start
and this very well could be,
if he wins, this very well could
be the fourth straight week
on the PGA Tour that we have these really
surprising great winners,
so I'm always about that.
I love the underdog,
I love the unexpected,
so I'm really, really,
really cheering for Redman.
- All right, sounds good.
Anita, thanks for the
insight, enjoy your holiday,
and you'll be back obviously,
on the show, on Friday.
- Yes, I'll be in for you, Doug,
so hopefully, you have a great weekend.
- [Doug] Oh, I will, hit the road.
And straight ahead on this show though,
the greatest emcee in sports, George Shea,
will break down tomorrow's
Hot Dog Eating Contest.
- And to me, that's the
greatest honor of this sport,
is to be able to introduce
Joey Chestnut because to me,
he is America itself,
to me, he is freedom,
he is the essence of who we are.
(upbeat music)
(dogs barking)
- What about him?
♪ I know ♪
- Let's do it.
♪ These winding roads ♪
♪ Will lead me home ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ And I'll go ♪
- [Woman] Come on!
- [Advertiser] This summer,
add a new member to the family.
Hurry into the Mercedes-Benz Summer Event
today for exceptional offers.
Lease the GLC 300 SUV
for just $419 a month
through Mercedes-Benz
Summer Event, going on now.
- [Announcer] You wanna stay
cool when you're feeling hot
but running your air
conditioner all day costs a lot.
Fans are bulky and just
blow hot air in your face.
There has to be a better
way to cool down your place.
Introducing Arctic Air,
the personal space cooler
that turns hot spaces into
cool refreshing places
for just pennies a day,
whether you wanna cool off
in a hot kitchen or stay
nice and comfy, watching TV,
Arctic Air let's you create
your own personal comfort zone.
Just add water and press the button.
Then relax and enjoy the cooling breeze.
Look, portable air conditioners
take up so much space
and have to vent out a
window but Arctic Air
is self contained and light weight.
So now, you can have
cool clean air anywhere.
Even the intense heat of this
blow dryer reads at 96 degrees
but with Arctic Air,
it's a comfortable 72.
The secret is hydro-chill technology
that uses an evaporative
air cooling filter
that pulls in hot air and instantly
transforms it into cool refreshing air,
with three adjustable speed settings,
you have precise control
and the whisper quiet fan
circulates the air up to eight
hours on just one filling.
And there's even a soothing night light.
What a great way to cool off your bedroom
without air conditioning your entire home.
Arctic Air also purifies
and humidifies your air,
so it's better for you and your family.
Plus, you can even beat the heat outdoors
and enjoy a cool refreshing
breeze, even on the hottest day.
You could pay up to $180
for a similar product
but call now and you'll get the Arctic Air
for just two payments of $19.99.
But wait, call right now, and
we'll double the offer free,
just pay a separate fee,
and every order today gets free shipping.
Now, everyone in your family can stay cool
and comfortable with the Arctic Air.
That's right, you get two
Arctic Airs plus free shipping
for just two payments of $19.99.
- [Announcer] To order,
call 1-800-610-1314
or go online at
buyarcticair.com, don't delay,
call 1-800-610-1314 or go online
at buyarcticair.com, order now.
- Bro!
- I got this.
- Bro.
- Bro!
- Bros.
- Bro.
(bell dings)
(upbeat music)
- [All] Bro!
- Bro!
- Bro.
- Oh, bro.
- Bro!
- [Men] Bro.
- Later, bromies.
- Bros.
- Bro!
- [Advertiser] Stuber,
in theaters, July 12th.
- The ESPYS Auction is where you can bid
on once in a lifetime experiences like,
a private meet and greet
with J Lo or Dana White,
appear in a Vista Sports
Center commercial,
pitch Mark Cuban over lunch,
or join me on the set of SportsCenter.
That should be like a million dollars.
So bid now, at ebay.com/ESPN.
- [Doug] The championship is
set for the Women's World Cup.
Obviously, the Americans advanced today.
Netherlands gets a go in
the 99th minute, one-nil.
So that is your showdown, and Caesars,
just posting these odds, the Americans
minus 475 to hoist the trophy.
Now, three way betting will be out later,
but just to win, no matter when it occurs.
U.S., nearly a five to one favorite
over Netherlands, so, that is Sunday.
Let's get ready for tomorrow.
It is a staple on our Independence Day,
the Nathan's Hot Dog Eating Contest.
- And here is George Shea.
- Through meditation,
he learned that his spirit
animal is a bologna sandwich.
He has the body of Adonis,
but the eating habits
of Homer Simpson.
- Doh!
- He is not, as they say, book smart.
In fact, if you ask him to name a country
in Central America, he will say,
"Kansas?"
(timer buzzing)
The difficulty in his
marriage began after he named
his children Mild, Medium, and Hot.
His good cholesterol is low,
his bad cholesterol is high,
and his BMI is borderline presidential.
When we are young, we drink
our coffee with milk and sugar
and as we age, we drink it with milk only.
Then we drink it black, then
we drink it decaf, then we die.
Our next eatery is at decaf.
It is an honor to all those now living,
to behold this man.
He is the fortress at
the center of our nation.
Of one nation, under God!
Indivisible, he is
champion, Joey Chestnut!
("Star Spangled Banner")
- We're now pleased to
welcome in the voice
and the biggest
personality of the July 4th
Hot Dog Eating Contest, George Shea.
George, thanks so much
for taking the time.
- Oh, thank you for having me.
- All right, let's talk about it.
Look, you've been with this
event for three decades.
You are an expert of all
experts, so let's get into it.
Joey Chestnut, he is synonymous here,
a record 11 Mustard Belts.
Is there any chance he
does not win this event?
- Oh, I think there's absolutely
a chance he doesn't win,
but I think the odds
would be extremely low.
Not only is he dominant in the sport,
74 hot dogs and buns
last year, in 10 minutes,
but on top of that, I saw him today.
He looks absolutely in top
form, he's very trim, very fit.
He seems very healthy,
and rested, and confident,
so I think he's gonna be coming in strong.
But at any time, he could be beaten
and there are a couple guys, Geoff Esper
and Matt Stonie, who could take him down.
- Talk more about those two
contenders, if you will.
What makes them, what's the path
to their success and
beating Joey Chestnut?
- Well, both of them
have enormous capacity
and Geoffrey Esper actually,
has beaten Joey Chestnut,
if I'm correct, two times
in the last three weeks.
He got him in Hostess Donettes
and he got him in chicken
wings, he's a monster.
He's a relative rookie, second,
third year on the circuit.
I think he gets a little
bit of the jitters
going into the big contest
on the Fourth of July.
He ate 51 hot dogs to qualify.
Keep in mind, the qualifying
hot dogs are harder to eat,
so you really have to think
of him, up at a 60 mark or so.
Then there's also Matt Stonie,
he's really an internet star
now, a YouTube star, eight
million followers on YouTube.
He does a bunch of
challenges, enormous capacity,
enormous capacity, but
often people have said,
he doesn't prepare for
the contest and get ready.
There's a rumor our there,
and I can't vouch for it,
but he's really gunning for Joey this year
and he could bring some heat.
- Okay, a couple of things
to digest, forgive the pun.
Qualifying hot dogs are
harder to eat, why is that?
- Well, if you think of
it, you're at Nathan's,
you're at the, sort of
the mecca of hot dogs
and they're cooked, perfectly
cooked on the griddle.
And they're cooked to
come off of the griddle
about 10 or 15 minutes
prior to the contest.
So they're the perfect
temperature, they're warm,
they're not cold, they're not hot.
When you're out on the circuit,
you might be at a festival,
you might be at a ballpark,
but bringing the hot dogs in, in warmers.
They've been cooked a half
an hour, an hour before.
Sometimes they're not fully griddled.
They're just cooked or they're steamed
but they're not grilled as
they would be at Coney Island,
and as a result, they're
more difficult to eat
or it takes longer to eat those dogs.
- All right, fascinating
stuff on that fact.
As you mentioned earlier,
Chestnut ate 74 hot dogs last year.
Do you see him hitting that mark
or going past it this year, as well?
- Well you know, I absolutely
think he'll be around there.
There have been times
when things drop off,
it could be the temperature of the day,
it could be literally, the humidity.
Actually, when you have
a very, very dry day,
it can dry out the buns.
So even if they're only out
there for five or 10 minutes,
they have a different consistency.
The hot dogs can tighten
up more in the sun.
So the temperature could play a role.
- So, let's talk about the women's side.
Micki Sudo going for a
sixth straight Mustard Belt.
What are the chances in your eyes,
she does not make it six straight?
- I think they're low, the
chances that she does not win,
but there could be more variability
in her performance on that.
So I do think it's
possible that Juliet Lee
or Michelle Lesco could
make a real run at her.
- The whole spectacle is awesome.
I'm looking forward to
watching it on July 4th.
And George, it was an honor to
have you here and I'm looking
forward to watching your
performance, as well.
Thank you for taking the time.
- Thank you, thank you for having me.
- And on that note, we go to Prop Culture
to wrap up the show.
Joe Fortenbaugh joins
me now and Joe, look,
total of hot dogs on the men's division,
73 1/2 and this is interesting,
I love what emcee George Shea
just said about Matt Stonie,
who he's hearing grumblings,
that he's going to really
bring it this year in his,
of course, enormous capacity.
I've been tracking this
stuff for a long time,
when I worked in Las Vegas.
I got to do a live shot,
downtown with the one and only,
Joey Chestnut, and the
one and only, Kobayashi.
They were talking trash to
one another, a lot of fun.
I'm no expert but I'm saying
under 73 1/2, if I had to, Joe.
- Doug, let me start by congratulating you
on a tremendous interview,
Shades of David Frost and
Richard Nixon, no doubt.
Now, I'm going over 73 1/2 hot dogs
and I got Joey Chestnut
winning this thing.
Doug, Joey Chestnut lives here
in the Bay Area, where I live.
The land of kale, the land
of avocado toast, soda taxes.
If you even think about
having a cheeseburger,
they wanna cast you out
into the Pacific Ocean.
Beautiful area, no doubt,
but they are not too fond
of noshing 73 1/2 hot dogs in 10 minutes.
That's not how people
do things here and yet,
Joey Chestnut rises every day in the face
of that adversity and he
takes on his detractors.
Let's go back to 2015,
when he lost to Matt Stonie, 62 to 60.
Came back the next year to
set a record with 70 hot dogs,
came back the following year
to set a record with 72 hot dogs,
and then came back last year
to set another record with 74 hot dogs.
This guy is not worried
about his competition.
He's worried about history and
he has stated that his goal
is to knock down 80 hot
dogs in a single sitting.
Doug, I say to you,
God bless Joey Chestnut,
God bless America.
- (chuckles) And weather
on your side, Joe,
because it's gonna be a
humid day and George Shea
was just saying that, that
lends itself to the over,
because the buns won't dry out,
but then I didn't think of asking him,
a lot of the competitors
dip the buns in the water,
so I'm a little confused.
I have certain thresholds for expertise
on the Hot Dog Eating
Contest but I do know this,
I will be watching and this
isn't like those other sports,
like football and basketball,
where you only have to
watch the last few minutes.
You have to watch the beginning
because of George Shea
and all the introductions
and the pomp and circumstance, as well.
So, Joe, we appreciate it.
I know who you're rooting
for here, your home town guy,
and more importantly, happy Fourth of July
and enjoy your holiday, my friend.
And recapping our Best
Bets, Preston in Vegas,
Summer League, Grizzlies, minus 2 1/2.
Joe's on the underdog Giants, plus $1.20.
Stanford Steve laying
the $1.38 with the Yanks,
trying to bounce back in the Subway Series
and I'll lay the run and a
half with the red hot Dodgers.