- [Spokesperson]
Presidents' Day sales event.
Plus get up to 125% of KBB with EasyTrade.
Limited time savings are here
during our Presidents' Day sales event.
♪ Sheehy.com ♪
(clicking)
- Track the winter weather with me
and search for the WUSA9
app in your app store.
(uptempo music)
- We're gonna time out hour
by hour when the snow moves in
and we'll time out hour by
hour when it turns to sleet
and freezing rain.
- This is just a terrible tragedy.
I mean, children are so
scarred by this crime.
- Do you think Bryce Harper's coming back?
- You know, part of me says
no and a part of me says yes.
- Hello, I'm Bruce Johnson,
thanks for joining us.
Welcome to OffScript.
Got lots to talk about.
I sat down with noted
scholar and Jesuit priest,
Father Thomas Reese earlier today
for an important conversation
about sexual abuse
in the Catholic Church.
That interview coming up
but first we need to bring
you up to date on the weather.
A red weather alert, here's Topper Shutt.
- Yeah and I want to emphasize,
we have trimmed the snowfall
totals a little bit.
That doesn't diminish
the impact of the storm.
It's sort of like focusing of
the hurricane, just on winds,
it has other elements that are dangerous
and this certainly does to
with sleet and freezing rain.
Three to five inches, plus.
Gattersburg, Frederick,
Leesburg, Martinsburg,
up towards Hagerstown, into the mountains.
One to three in the immediate
metro area, including D.C.
Chevy Chase, Buoy, Bethesda,
down to the south, southern
Maryland, not as much.
You were never gonna
have that much anyway.
A trace to an inch,
your cold air is just
simply lacking a little bit.
So what does that mean?
Well, it still means that
the roads are gonna be
a disaster as we get
into Wednesday morning.
RPM up to it's old tricks
again, going seven inches.
Everybody else has a grasp on reality
around two inches to three inches.
Which is where we settled
on in the metro area.
So what do we know?
Well we know that snowfall
will be moderate to heavy
six a.m. to noon,
and the roads will
become very treacherous.
And when it starts it's gonna
pick up in intensity quickly
and it's going to accumulate very quickly.
The snow will go to a mix north
and west in the afternoon.
And it will go to rain
D.C., south and east
in the afternoon.
And if we can get through the day
it'll turn to all rain tomorrow night.
After some morning showers on Thursday
we pop back in the 50's.
Look how much moisture is headed our way.
If this system were about
300 miles off to the east
we'd be looking at
another, a little blizzard.
But we're not so, five
o'clock in the morning.
Little bit of snow breaking
out in part of the metro area.
Temps, upper 20's, low 30's
becomes pretty much heavy to moderate
across the entire metro area.
This is by seven o'clock on Wednesday.
The temps are still 29, 30 degrees.
By the time we get to
ten o'clock we still have
heavy snow across the metro area.
And then it begins to mix and change
right around the lunch hour.
We will come back.
We will talk about how
much ice could accumulate
behind the snow and who we think
are most likely for power outages.
- Okay, let's talk some baseball here.
Manny Machado is getting 300 million.
What will Bryce Harper get?
Reports tonight say Machado has agreed
to sign with San Diego Padres.
Contract reportedly worth
$300 million over ten years.
The deal is reported to be pending
the results of a physical.
The former Baltimore Oriole's
and LA Dodgers infielder
is slated to play third
base for the Padre's.
Now, the attention turns to Bryce Harper.
Speculation about where he'll end up
is all over social media tonight.
Will he resign with the Nationals?
Most of us don't think so.
The latest rumors have
him going to Philadelphia.
The Nats player's already
in spring training camp
down in Florida.
Darrin Haynes sat down with
Nats manager Dave Martinez
to talk about Bryce.
- How much do you want Bryce on your team?
- You know what, Bryce and I
have a special relationship.
I mean, everybody knows that.
Who wouldn't want Bryce
Harper on their team?
Honestly, I mean, he's one
of the best young players
in the game, you know.
And you know for me it's
all about what he wants now.
You know, for his family and
his career, it really is.
So, I mean, he's got
big decisions to make.
You know, but I'd be be wrong to say that,
of course you know, anybody
would want him on his team.
He makes a big difference.
- If Bryce decided hey, you know what,
I'm coming back to the Nationals.
What would be your reaction
when he walks in the door?
- Hey, I'd be like hey,
welcome back, you know.
- That's it, that's it huh.
- Time to work, you know.
Let's go to work, you know .
- Do you think Bryce Harper's coming back?
- You know part of me says
no and a part of me says yes.
You know, you just, the way
this game is you just don't,
you really don't know.
- Which way are you leaning towards?
- I you know what, I honestly
I, like I said, I can't,
I can't lean either way.
It's so weird because of, you know.
You know like I said,
you know, and I try to,
you know I try like
say hey, you know what,
this is what I gotta do today you know.
I gotta lead 59 guys tomorrow morning.
Get up at six o'clock,
get to that ballpark
and get the day going you know.
My focus is on the day at
hand and the here and now and
that's kind of what I worry about.
- Eat your food man.
(laughing)
- Thanks Darrin.
Is Martinez playing us?
How does he not know?
Joining me to discuss all
this column is Mike Wise.
How does he not know
what Bryce is gonna do?
- I think, I don't know if he does
because I think there's
this big question mark here.
Manny Machado just signed for
the largest free agent deal
in the history of American
sports, not just baseball.
And there's a big pressure on Scott Boras,
who is Bryce's agent to go at
least one dollar over that.
The Nationals have already
offered 300 million.
I don't know if that offer
is even there any more
for ten years.
So this is, I think what
Dave Martinez is thinking is,
has Ted Lerner broke his
dependency with Scott Boras
whom he's got all this,
he had a bunch of his clients before.
Can he say no to Scott Boras this time.
And I think that's gonna be the question.
Personally, I kind of want Bryce to stay.
I really do, I think
he's Q-Rating in town.
He's star power.
- We like stars.
I mean he puts people in the seats--
- We do like stars.
- He puts jerseys on the kids' backs.
That sort of thing.
But what do you think?
Whatcha got?
- My gut is that the Phillies
are gonna offer something so enormous.
One person said nine years, 367 million.
I don't know if that's
gonna happen or not.
I do know that the Nationals
will be given a chance to counter.
I can't see them going over
350 million, I just can't.
You know, just based on their payroll,
just based on what they've
got committed already.
But I don't know, you know, I don't know.
That could be a wild card.
- What you haven't mentioned,
the Nats already have a team.
They have somebody in
Bryce's position right now.
Does that matter?
- They have Robles, they got Juan Soto,
those are guys that are gonna
definitely take his spot at the plate.
They're not gonna be Bryce Harper.
Bryce Harper was a live wire.
He was like a hand grenade.
He was a,
you didn't know when he was gonna explode.
- And we don't need to see him.
- And he was the most
exciting thing in sports
in Washington for a while.
- And we don't nee to see
him in a Phillies uniform.
They already bring
thousands of fans down here
every time they play the Nats.
- Philly fans are the worst.
- Ha!
- And I love you Selika.
I know you, I work with you,
Philly fans are the worst.
- All right, okay, she works here.
All right, Mike Wise, thanks
a lot man, appreciate it.
- All right.
- Okay, flip the page.
Sexual abuse scandals have
shaken the Catholic Church
at its core.
For us it starts here in Washington D.C.
where former cardinal and
Archbishop Theodore McCarrick
has been defrocked by the Pope.
He is now only Mr. McCarrick
and living in a remote
monastery somewhere out there
in the Midwest.
To Argentina, where the New
York Times is reporting,
deaf children were
sexually abused for years
by the priests who should
have been caring for them.
You probably now that Pope
Francis this week will begin
a summit of bishops and cardinals
who have been called to Rome to fix this.
But can they, will they?
Today I talk with Father Thomas Reese.
He's a noted Jesuit priest and scholar
who is on his way to Rome.
Father Reese first off
tell me why you're
going to Rome right now.
- I'm going to Rome because
the Pope has called a meeting
of the top bishops from around the world
to come and talk to him
about the sex abuse crisis.
He wants to emphasis to
them how important it is
to protect children and their
responsibility to do that.
And I think he's gonna make
the point that if they don't,
if they're not responsible
he's going to hold them accountable.
So this is gonna be an important meeting
for the Catholic Church
because it's the first meeting like this
that's ever happened.
- Yeah, let's talk about
some of the headlines.
I mean, just today, the
Washington Post is reporting
that deaf children were sexually abused
by priests in Argentina.
What do you make of this?
Is this gonna come up in Rome?
- This is, I mean this is
just a terrible tragedy.
I mean, children are so
scarred by this crime.
This abuse that they suffer under.
And that's why the church
has to have a policy
to deal with it.
You know, in the United
States we've had a zero policy
on abuse of children.
And in fact in the church
we've had this policy of zero tolerance.
So that anybody, any
priest involved in abuse
is removed from the priesthood
and could never act as a priest again.
Now the second part is to make sure that
all the bishops implement this policy.
Make it happen and that's
gonna be an important message
at this meeting.
- Father Reese talk to me
about the apparent hypocrisy
in all of this.
It's come out today in
a New York Times article
that the Vatican has a book,
has rules on what to do with children
who are fathered by priests.
Who knew?
- Well I think that the,
actually when you look at the document
from the reports that I've seen,
the emphasis in the document is on
the priests responsibility for his child.
Pope Francis has said this in the past.
He said that even before he became Pope.
And that is that if a
priest fathers a child
then he has a responsibility as a father.
Not, you know, financial responsibility
and also just as a father.
As a paternal responsibility
and that that responsibility supersedes
his responsibility to be a priest.
And he needs to leave the
priesthood and raise that child.
(uptempo music)
- [Bruce] Coming up,
my conversation with Father
Thomas Reese continues.
We're gonna talk about gay priests.
(slow instrumental music)
- [Announcer] Ovechkin shoots and scores.
- [TV Personality] Come cheer
on your Washington Capital's
at Capital One Arena.
- [Announcer] Saved one by Holtby.
(audience cheering)
- Let's go Caps!
- [TV Personality] Single
game tickets are on sale now.
- [Announcer] And he scores!
- [TV Personality] For more
information call 202-266-CAPS
or visit washcaps.com/tickets.
Capital One cardholders
receive a 10% discount.
- [Woman] Update your floors
with Luna's $50 room sale.
Buy one room,
get floors for all other
rooms for just $50 each.
So when you buy one room,
it's only $50 for laminating the kitchen.
$50 for carpet in the bedroom
and $50 for hardwood in the office.
There's not limit.
Buy one room and it's $50 for floors
in each additional room.
Visit luna.com or call
♪ 877 241 LUNA ♪
- [Man] Fourth of July has it's fireworks.
Christmas, gifts.
But what about Presidents' Day?
Let's just say the voters
will be very happy.
Announcing our best offers on
America's best selling brand.
You gotta love democracy.
- [Salesman] Through February 28th only,
get 4,000 total cash on select Ford SUV's.
Hurry to your local Ford
dealers for best selection
during the Presidents' Day sales event.
- [Man] Get ready to crave
Checkers and Rally's because
Texas toast garlic bread.
Four of the greatest words, ever.
Put that toast on two juicy patties
with all the fix-ins for a classic double.
Or cover it with crispy
onions dripping with
sweet smokey barbecue.
Then drop the garlicky buttery mic.
Because you just won at eating.
For only $2.99, new Texas
Toast Garlic Bread Doubles.
Checkers and Rally's.
Fast foodies know the deal.
- Don't go through another
cold winter this year
with those old, open top
gutters that clog, freeze, warp
and fall off your home.
Eliminate climbing the
ladders to clean the gutters,
especially in the winter time.
Look at LeafGuard.
The only one piece
rainwater management system.
20% thicker than the competition,
50% bigger downspouts.
Ask about our clog free guarantee.
And now would be a great
time to give us a call
to take advantage of these
special winter savings
on LeafGaurd.
It's our 60-60-60 sale.
Look at the 60% off labor
if you call right now.
We're gonna work it
out to fit your budget.
Payments as low as $60 a month
and if you call in today,
you get a $60 Visa gift card
with the purchase of LeafGuard.
Take a look at LeafGuard.
The water goes in, keeps
out the leaves, pine needles
and other debris with a
lifetime transferable warranty.
And if you call now you
get a $25 Lowe's gift card
with your complimentary in-home estimate.
Pick up the phone and
call LeafGuard today.
- Welcome back to OffScript.
The Pope has summoned church
leaders from around the world
to meet at the Vatican as
the church is now in crisis.
Will they address the
issue of gay priests?
Let's continue the conversation
with noted Jesuit priest
and scholar Father Thomas Reese.
It's a Skype interview
and this part of the
connection wasn't as clear
but we think it's that important.
What about the whole issue of gay priests?
I was in the seminary a hundred years ago,
there were 13 guys in my class.
Only one went the entire 13
years and became a priest
and I know that John was gay, okay.
We've known all along that
there are gay priests.
If it were up to a lot of Catholics
there would be openly gay priests.
There would be women priests.
There would be married priests
who could then have children.
When is the Church gonna come to this
or is this just wishful thinking?
- The first important thing to say is
that there are a lot of
wonderful gay priests
in the priesthood.
Priests who, gay priests who
observe their vow of celibacy
and are very good pastoral priests.
We don't wanna mix up
the issue of gay priests
with the issue of sexual abuse of minors.
And I, you know, that needs to,
that point needs to be made.
But I agree with you.
I think we need more
honesty in the church.
For example, the US bishops
have never allowed anybody
to survey priests to find out, you know,
what percentage of them are gay.
We've got estimated from
10, 20, 30, 40, 50, 60.
I mean, all over the place.
And nobody's got any real data.
The one fact we do know is that
there are gay priests
there and most of them,
you know, are good priests
who observe their promise
of celibacy and are good for the church.
- Do you expect anything
to come of this meeting
or is this just gonna
be more window dressing?
- [Thomas] I think that most Americans
are gonna be disappointed
with this meeting.
Because we would like to
see policies and procedures
set up and structures to
hold bishops accountable.
I think the truth of the matter is
that this meeting is
primarily for other countries
where bishops are in total denial.
They don't think they have this problem.
They think this is an American problem.
And basically the message we want to take
to these bishops is,
don't make the same mistakes
that the American bishops made.
You know, get your act together now.
Remove these bad crazies and reach out
and help the victims in healing.
- But Father Reese it's
not just the priests,
we're seeing Theodore McCarrick,
right here in Washington.
Who has become the poster
child for this kind of abuse.
So it's not just the priests,
the bishops are being
asked to police themselves.
Are they not?
- No, I think that you know,
this is very important and
needs to be dealt with.
McCarrick because he was a retired bishop,
you know, they brought the
information to the Vatican
and the Vatican said,
okay treat him just
like you would a priest
of the archdiocese of New York.
So his case was investigated.
They hired a forensic research team.
The information was presented
to the lay review board
and they said the
accusations were credible
and substantiated and he
was removed from, you know,
he was removed.
And he had to resign his being a cardinal
and now he's been removed
from the priesthood.
He's not, now he can no
longer be Father McCarrick
or Bishop McCarrick, he is Mr McCarrick.
- [Bruce] Yeah.
- He can never act as a priest again.
- This is exactly what should happen.
- Father Reese good luck on your trip.
Look forward to your reporting.
- Thank you, good to be with you.
- And Washington's
current Archbishop Donald
is obviously leaving.
We don't have any word tonight
on who will succeed him.
If you're just tuning in
and you missed part one
of our interview, both segments
will be posted on wusa9.com
right after this broadcast.
It's an important conversation
so you wanna make sure to check it out.
Coming up.
Topper Shutt issuing a red
weather alert for tomorrow.
He'll have the very latest timeline
on when you should be off the roads.
Coming up next.
(slow instrumental music)
- [Man] Tonight,
- What do we got?
- [Man] NCIS has a surprise so good,
missing it would be criminal.
- Your computer is trying to--
- Take down the Department of Defense.
- [Man] New NCIS, then.
- Looks like a professional hit.
- [Man] The search for answers
leads to more questions.
- Who hired you?
- [Man] A new FBI after
a new NCIS, CBS tonight.
- [Man] Tonight.
- If you get this send help!
- [Man] One journalist under siege,
when conspiracy uncovered.
- We got another to go on.
- [Man] NCIS New Orleans tonight.
- [Announcer] Fourth of
July has its fireworks.
Christmas, gifts.
But what about Presidents' Day?
Let's just say the voters
will be very happy.
Announcing our best offers on
America's best selling brand.
You gotta love democracy.
Through February 28th
only get 4000 total cash
on select Ford SUVs.
Hurry to your local Ford
dealers for best selection
during the Presidents' Day sales event.
(upbeat music)
- [Woman] Dinnertime Drew.
You're just going to begin tomorrow.
- Told you moving won't be so bad.
- Yep.
- Later dude.
- [Man] Whatever tomorrow's
technology you'll be ready
because Cox is building a new
gig speed network to bring you
the internet of the future.
- This Presidents' Day there's
big news, at Nissan now.
No brand received more J.D.
Power initial quality awards
for cars and trucks than Nissan.
That means that people
love their new Nissans.
So we're thanking you with
big savings on our lineup,
including Rogue, with ProPilot Assist.
- [Announcer] For a limited
time save up to 3500
on the 2019 Rogue or the 2019 Sentra.
- Get a Nissan now before these
offers are yesterday's news.
- Clogged gutters this winter
can do more damage to your home
than you realize from the
door jams to your landscaping.
That's why more and more
homeowners are making the switch
to LeafGuard, the gutter
that never clogs guaranteed.
Take advantage of our 60-60-60 sale.
60% off labor, payments
as low as $60 a month,
$60 Visa gift card is
a bonus with purchase.
And if you call right
now $25 Lowe's gift card
with your complimentary in
home estimate from LeafGuard.
Call today.
- Track the winter weather with me
and search the WUSA9
app in your app store.
Alright, we're looking at a
red weather alert for the snow,
for the sleet and also
for the freezing rain.
All right here is a look
at our snowfall maps.
Three to five Leesburg,
Gaithersburg, Frederick,
points north and west.
In the metro, one to three.
These are a little lower than yesterday.
Yes, because we're thinking
more sleet and less snow
and then to Southern Maryland,
y'all never had that much coming anyway,
trace to an inch there.
Notice there's a plus sign out here.
Some of you folks in that band could get
conceivably over five inches of snow,
which is gonna be a problem
as it kicks to rain.
So we're kinda worried about that.
We'll get back to this in a second.
Look, but we look forward to 66 on Sunday.
We gotta get through
some things to get there.
So here we some.
All right, GFS, European model.
Pretty much in agreement with us
around three inches downtown.
That seems reasonable,
look at the moisture.
This is crazy.
I mean for Wichita, Kansas,
all the way to Cape Hatteras,
it was snow extending up into Iowa
and also South Dakota and Nebraska.
That's a big storm.
So on the broad-o-meter I
do kind of reserve these for
pure snows but because this
is gonna be a legitimate snow
with some sleet and freezing rain
and enough snow on the front end too.
That'd be plowable and sledable.
In terms of the impact,
well, we know it's coming so hopefully
folks will just stay off the
road but nonetheless still
we're gonna give it a 3.5 in
the impact-o-meter as well.
So it's certainly a legitimate storm.
Now I have updated this,
this is on our website.
I just tweeted this out.
In terms of power outages
and here's why I did this.
Isolated along I-95 and
points west, unlikely east
and then scattered out in
Cumberland, Romney and Hagerstown
where we think significant
icing will occur.
But here's the deal, either
where icing won't occur
if we get three inches of snow in DC,
plain old fashioned rain will
add to the weight of that snow
and could bring down limbs as well.
So we may see power outages,
not just confined to those
areas that pick up ice.
Alright, this is one model,
most of the ice far to the west
and not that bad, Petersburg three tenths
and about two tenths in Romney.
We can probably handle that.
This is gonna be tough.
This is now almost an inch
of ice outdoor Cumberland,
three tenths Leesburg,
three tenths Gaithersburg
that would cause some
power outages no doubt.
Why is it not a pure snow?
Well we start out with the pure snow
'cause this column of air
is all below freezing.
But then we get warm air
as it moves into the middle
layers of the atmosphere
either becomes sleet which
is the bouncy pieces of ice
but freezing rain is what
we're most concerned about,
falls liquid and then
just freezes on contact.
So this hasn't changed
too much from yesterday.
We adjusted the time a bit.
Heavier snows 6 a.m. to noon.
Roads will become dangerous.
It will start quickly,
become intense quickly
and accumulate quickly.
It will go to a mixed north
and west in the afternoon.
It will go to rain DC, south
and east in the afternoon.
And heavy rain possible overnight
and then showers then we're
in the 50's on Thursday.
How about that?
So 6 a.m. tomorrow,
there's a snow across
most of the metro area.
Notice the shades of blue,
the darker the blue, heavier snow.
Pretty much thumping at nine o'clock,
no doubt but that begins to turn
as we get toward the lunch hour,
especially down to the south
and then just plain old
rain DC, south and east
by about three o'clock.
Some lingering freezing
rain north and west
until the evening, so here we go.
Red alert on Wednesday, 56,
morning showers Thursday
and then nice on Friday, 54.
In terms of the snow once again,
we're looking again three
to five north and west
and one to three in the metro
and about trace to an inch
south and east.
Bruce will be back after this.
(slow instrumental music)
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Next ET Miranda's
wedding secrets unveiled
plus Megan's baby shower in New York, and
- I'm exclusively in London
with Victoria Beckam.
- [Narrator] Next ET.
- [Woman] Tonight at 7:30 on WUSA9.
- I'm looking at that truck.
- Wow.
- That's awesome.
- [Man] Everyone is
excited about the all new
award winning Chevy models.
- They're all really cool cars.
- I love it.
- I can't stop staring at it.
- [Man] See what the
excitement's all about
at your local Chevy dealer
and take advantage of
a great deal like this.
Current qualified competitive
lessees can lease this Malibu
for around 179 a month,
or current GM owners
get 4250 total cash allowance
on most Malibu models
when you purchase and
finance with GM Financial.
♪ Pay the price ♪
- You pay too much.
♪ O' loving you ♪
- For your glasses, they
charged you too much.
- Who?
- Practically anyone
who isn't America's Best
wear two pairs and a
free exam for just 69.95.
- That sounds good.
- Music to your ears.
- Speaking of, do you wanna join?
- I'm not really a singer.
- Do you whistle?
- [Man] It's not just a better
deal, it's America's best.
Never overpay even with insurance.
Get more with your
vision insurance dollars
at America's Best.
(hooting)
- Sorry.
- We all know how it can
be to go to the wrong place
for transmission repair.
- My (bleep) dealer should
just fix this transmission.
- [Man] So don't risk it, take
it to the experts at AAMCO.
- Just to shift to Illinois, no biggie.
- (bleep) is Illinois?
(woman laughing)
- [Man] AA, (hooting) MCO.
Check engine light on,
we'll check it for free.
- Hi Ron Sherman back again for LeafGuard.
They tell us that thousands
of accidents happen each day
nationwide up on ladders.
It's really dangerous in the wintertime
and they say us folks over 60
have more than our fair
share of ladder accidents.
So let me keep you safe with LeafGuard.
The only one piece
rainwater management system
with a clog free guarantee.
- The ladder, the extension
ladder slipped out from under me
and I wound up upside
down hanging from my leg
on the extension ladder
and that wasn't too good.
- We can give you peace
of mind with LeafGuard.
Look at LeafGuard, the gutter
the never clogs guaranteed.
Take advantage of our 60-60-60 sale.
It's not too late to get LeafGuard
on your home this winter.
60% off labor, payments
as low as $60 a month,
$60 Visa gift card with purchase.
$25 Lowe's gift card with your estimate
if you call right now during
this program, last chance.
Pick up the phone and
call LeafGuard today.
- Because of the wintry
weather we're expecting
the Wake Up Washington team
will be on early tomorrow.
We're talking 4 a.m. with
the latest on conditions
and closings because of the storm.
I'm on Twitter at brucejohnson9,
Facebook Bruce Johnson WUSA9.
We'll see you back here tomorrow.
Have a great evening everybody, bye.
(slow instrumental music)
- [Woman] You've been watching WUSA9 news.
With a weather forecast
rated most accurate
for the last seven years.
(upbeat music)
- Here's your Buick sir.
- Actually, that's my Buick.
- Your Buick doesn't have a roof rack?
- This is my Buick.
- How are we gonna fit your mom's Buick?
- Easy.
- I like that new Buick.
- Me too.
- I was actually talking about that Buick.
- I knew that.
- Did you?
- [Man] Buick's fresh new
lineup is full of surprises.
Get great deals on our
expectation shattering lineup.
Pay no interest for 72
months on most Buick models.
(upbeat music)
- [Man] Stay warm and cozy
with gasfireplaces.com.
Cyprus Air's Presidents' Day Sale is here.
Convert your wood burning fireplace to gas
and get up to 80% off
with installation as early as next week.
Visit your nearest showroom
or schedule a free in home visit online
at gas.fireplaces.com.
- [Woman] Stronger is
rebuilding a newborn's heart
and restoring a father's faith.
It's standing tall after
one surgery, not six.
Stronger is being a typical
kid, despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding it earlier
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is seeking
answers and not giving up
until you find them.
Because we don't just
want your kids to grow up,
we want them to grow up stronger.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Tonight.
Meghan Markle's baby shower.