(lively music)
- [Show Announcer] WETA
is proud to present
the PBS NewsHour in HD.
(triumphant music)
- Good evening, I'm Judy Woodruff.
On the NewsHour tonight, A House Divided.
President Trump delivers his
State of the Union address
after the longest government shutdown
and no deal yet in sight for a
barrier at the southern border.
We talk with lawmakers.
Historian Michael Beschloss
puts the address in context,
and our panel previews what
is at stake for the President.
Plus, Mr. Trump's plan
to keep forces in Iraq
to monitor Iran sparked
condemnation in Baghdad
and calls for the U.S. to leave.
All that and more on
tonight's PBS NewsHour.
(upbeat music)
- [Show Announcer] Major
funding for the PBS NewsHour
has been provided by:
- [Narrator] On a cruise
with American Cruise Lines,
travelers experience the maritime heritage
and culture of New England.
Our fleet of small cruise ships
explores American
landscapes, seaside villages,
and historic harbors
where you can experience
local customs and cuisine.
American Cruise Lines, proud
sponsor of PBS NewsHour.
(beeping)
- Ordering takeout.
- Finding the best route.
- [Both] Talking for hours.
- Planning for showers.
- [Announcer] You can do
the things you like to do
with a wireless plan designed for you
with talk, text, and data.
Consumer Cellular.
Learn more at ConsumerCellular.tv.
- [Narrator] BNSF Railway.
- [Announcer] Babbel, a language program
that teaches Spanish, French,
Italian, German, and more.
- [Show Announcer] And
with the ongoing support
of these institutions.
(uplifting music)
This program was made possible by the
Corporation for Public Broadcasting
and by contributions to your PBS station
from viewers like you.
Thank you.
(uplifting music)
- This is State of the Union night,
when the President makes an annual report
to the American people,
but it comes at a time
of division here in Washington.
The White House says President
Trump will appeal for unity
even as he holds to his
demand for a border wall.
Newly resurgent Democrats say
the President himself is the problem.
The split was clear at the Capitol today
as Mr. Trump's supporters
and opponents sounded off.
- I think he's doing a good job,
and I think he really is making an effort.
He'll make some statements tonight
that'll surprise a lot of
people on the other side.
I'm talking about conciliatory things
and I think this comes from the heart.
This guy is, he has a background that has
shown him in different lights
but it's always been successful.
- Well, the President
hasn't been acting on unity
for two years up and down the line.
He's always criticizing, dividing,
and so if he calls for unity
tonight, we'll have to say,
let's see what happens tomorrow
and the day after and the day after,
because in the past he's called for unity
and he's forgotten about
it by the next morning.
- The formal Democratic response tonight
will come from Stacey Abrams of Georgia.
She narrowly lost her bid last year
to become that state's
first Black governor
and she's now a rising star
in the Democratic Party.
Let's turn now to our Lisa
Desjardins at the Capitol
and Yamiche Alcindor at the White House
watching all of this.
Yamiche, to you first.
I've been talking to
folks at the White House,
much of it off the record.
You've been talking to them too.
What do we know for certain,
or what do we think the
President's gonna focus on tonight?
- The President's gonna
focus on unifying our nation
and unifying both political parties,
but some of course say that there's some
credibility issues there because of
his political track record of really
offending and giving insults
to his political opponents.
The President is expected to talk about
a number of topics including
illegal immigration,
health care costs, including trade,
wars and foreign policy,
as well as infrastructure.
He's supposed to be, at some point,
pitching and asking Congress to come up
with some sort of infrastructure plan.
The President's also
supposed to be talking about
HIV and trying to end the transmission of
that deadly disease by 2030,
and the President is also
supposed to be talking about
his ideas for a way forward,
and it's really important
though to remind people
that the President has been tweeting today
and he's been saying
that Chuck Schumer's mad
that he didn't win the Senate.
He's also said in the past that
Democrats don't believe
in border security,
so while the President puts
forward this unifying message,
there are people who are saying,
well, just look at what you tweeted today.
That's gonna be hurting
that unifying message.
- And Lisa, we know that the other party
always prepares for what
the President's gonna say.
What are Democrats saying
about how they plan to handle,
what they expect the President to say
and how they're gonna respond to it?
- I have to tell you, Judy,
Democrats are more excited
about this response
than I've heard them in some time.
Stacey Abrams, to them, represents a
shift away from playing it safe.
In fact, there's one long-time
progressive who told me tonight,
we've been playing it
too safe as Democrats.
We want someone who has a
clear, aggressive agenda
like Stacey Abrams, who
talks about voter rights.
She also represents some other
important themes for Democrats tonight.
Diversity, in two ways.
One, she will be the first
African-American woman
to give a major party response.
Also, though, she will be the
first non-elected official.
She no longer holds office,
having lost the
gubernatorial race last fall.
She'll be the first non-elected official
to give this kind of response,
so a sort of outsider
and also a core part
of the Democratic base.
This also speaks to a theme
that we'll see visually
on the floor, Judy.
Democratic women in the House
will be wearing all white.
They say that is to show kind of a sign,
reference to the suffragettes,
but it also, one of them told
me, is a smart visual cue.
They want to highlight the difference
between Democrats and
their increased diversity
in this Congress, and Republicans who have
less diversity this Congress.
- And Lisa, staying with you,
Yamiche mentioned the
President is supposed
to talk tonight about border security.
What do we know at this point about
where the conference committee
working on that issue for
the last several days.
They have a deadline facing them.
I talked today to Speaker Pelosi
and Minority Leader Schumer,
they said they think
progress is being made.
What are you hearing?
- My reporting is the same.
Talking to other leaders
and people who are
on the conference committee,
there is real progress.
On the staff level, they think they could
come up with a deal if it is just left
to the members of the
Appropriations Committee alone.
Judy, the conference committee will have
an unusual meeting tomorrow morning,
closed doors, with career
Border Patrol officials.
Now, it's not clear why
that's to be closed doors,
but one staffer told me
they think it's because
they want the questions and answers to be
as forthright as possible.
They are looking at trying
to get a conference report
by the end of this week or
this weekend at the latest.
They think it's doable, but
there are many X-factors,
one of the biggest being the President
and what he says tonight
about border security.
- And finally, Yamiche,
what do we know about
how the President is planning for tonight,
and also traditionally the President
has guests come to the Capitol.
Who do we know those to be?
- Well, the President is going to be using
this national stage to make the case
that the state of the union is great,
but that it would be better
if there were concerns met
and concerns, and people paid attention
to the concerns that he had.
Right behind me at the White House,
the President has been preparing
and really using this speech as a way to
prepare himself to talk on a teleprompter.
He had a teleprompter
actually brought into
the White House so he's gonna be trying to
make sure that he's reading properly.
The other thing that he's gonna be doing
is bringing in guests here.
The guests that he's bringing in are
one, a family that was,
whose family member
was murdered or killed by
an undocumented immigrant.
The President's also going to be bringing
a little boy named Joshua Trump
who was bullied because of his last name
who, of course, he shares
with the President,
and the President's also
going to be bringing
someone who was freed by the
Criminal Justice Reform Act
that was passed by both
parties, of course,
supporting that bill, so the
President's gonna be saying,
we want bipartisanship
and look at this person
who came out of prison, he is embodying
what we could be doing in the future.
- Yamiche Alcindor at the White House,
Lisa Desjardins at the Capitol,
and we'll certainly be
coming back to the two of you
as the State of the Union gets underway
later tonight when we
have our special coverage.
Thanks,
and we wanna hear from lawmakers now.
Representative James
Clyburn of South Carolina
is the third highest ranking
Democrat in the U.S. House,
and he joins us from Capitol Hill.
Representative Clyburn, thank
you very much for joining us.
- Thank you.
What are you looking for
President Trump to say tonight?
- Well, the President is
asking us to choose greatness,
and I would hope that we
hear some greatness from him,
but you know, I have been
reading a lot of Joyce,
of Alexis de Tocqueville of late,
and Alexis de Tocqueville,
in one of his writings,
Democracy in America, told us that
America's greatness is not because
we are more enlightened
than any other country,
but because we've always been
able to repair our faults.
I would hope that the President tonight
will demonstrate that kind of greatness,
propose some things that we
can do to repair our faults.
They have been highlighted quite a bit
in the last several
months, and I am hopeful
that whatever he says tonight
will bring us together
as a people, move us forward as a country,
and make us really the
genius of greatness.
- Well, where do you
see, Congressman Clyburn,
there could be common ground,
because what the White House says is,
we've tried to make overtures
to Democrats on border security.
We haven't, they haven't
met eye to eye with us,
and they tick off a number of other issues
where they say Democrats haven't
been able to meet them halfway.
What do you, where do you
see potential common ground?
- Well, I think there's common ground
to be had on border security.
The President seems to have backed away
from his concrete 30-foot high wall
and is now talking about
more border security,
he's talking about barriers,
and we too have backed
away from our positions
of no money for any kind of wall.
We are advocating a smart wall,
using 21st century
technology to make this wall
as smart as we've made our
telephones and our televisions,
so we can have a smart wall,
one that would use drones
to keep anybody from flying over it,
use X-ray equipment to keep
anybody from getting around it,
use scanners to keep anybody
from burrowing under it undetected.
So we can do this in a smart way.
I just came back from Brownsville, Texas.
We were at a port of entry,
and I saw a port in dire
need of retrofitting.
I saw the fencing that's already there
in dire need of repairing.
I do believe that we can do
what is necessary to secure our border.
Just do it in a smart way,
not to build a monument to anybody.
- So to be clear, you're saying Democrats,
and obviously as we said,
you're third in line
in the leadership in the House,
the Democrats are prepared to support
the money for some sort
of physical barrier?
- I said so long as it's done smartly.
I believe that we will vote for
whatever that committee comes out.
If they come out with
a bipartisan approach
to get this done, irrespective
of how they put it together,
I do believe you'll get extensive support
among Democrats for it.
It may not be unanimous,
but it'll be a lot of unity.
- Are Democrats prepared to show
respect to the President tonight?
I ask that because we remember
under President Obama,
there were State of the Union addresses
when members called out to him,
once one of them calling him a liar.
How do you see tonight going?
- I think you'll see us
being very respectful.
You know, my dad used
to teach us all the time
that the first sign of a good education
is good manners and so I try to put
my education on display every time I walk
into the halls of the Congress,
or the House of Representatives.
You may remember, when that yell was made,
I'm the one that led the charge
to get a resolution of disapproval
for what my colleague said that night
and it passed the House of Representatives
and I think that we showed then
that we disapprove of such actions
and we certainly are
not going to do anything
to violate what we did last year.
- Congressman Clyburn, finally,
what other areas do you see
Democrats and Republicans
and the White House working
together on this year?
- Oh, I think that we can do
a comprehensive infrastructure deal.
I think we know that it's necessary
for us to develop our rural communities.
We need to be putting in water and sewage.
We need to be repairing roads and bridges.
We need to be building
schools in our rural areas.
We can do a comprehensive
bill that would have
broadband deployment going
into these rural communities.
Too many of them are being left behind.
We need to make this investment.
It will pay off handsomely if we do,
and I really believe it can
be done in a bipartisan way.
- Congressman James
Clyburn, who is the whip
for the Democrats in the
House of Representatives.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- And as we heard,
President Trump is expected
to double down in his speech tonight,
calling on Congress to fund a wall,
a barrier along the southern border.
One option he has not ruled out,
declaring a national
emergency to build the wall.
That is causing a split
among Senate Republicans.
Senator Lindsey Graham warned yesterday
that there could be a war
within the GOP over the wall.
We turn now to one of the President's
most loyal allies in Congress.
He is Senator David Perdue of Georgia.
Senator, thank you very
much for joining us,
and I think you are there.
There you are.
Senator, how much of a
divide is there still,
do you think, between
Republicans and Democrats,
between Democrats and the White House
over what is going to happen with regard
to a barrier, a wall
at the southern border?
- Well, I hope that it's narrowing, Judy.
I mean, this is a situation
where we're dealing
with a topic that both sides
are making the same argument.
This is the fifth President in a row
that's asked Congress for
border funding to build a wall.
H.W. Bush built the first miles,
even Barack Obama built 135 miles of wall.
Both parties agree that this
is a national security issue,
and we need to do it now.
The problem is the hypocrisy of politics
have brought us to this point.
I'm hopeful that this conference committee
is going to get to a
bipartisan solution here
that we can all support,
and I'm hopeful they will, Judy.
- Well, as you know Senator,
during the campaign over two years ago,
the President was talking about a wall.
At times he spoke about a concrete wall,
at times he spoke about
sea to shining sea.
The President has changed
what he's asking for,
isn't that fair to say?
- Well, this is a man who's, number one,
trying to protect the American people.
He's fighting for our national security.
There's 2,000 miles of
that southern border.
650 miles, Judy, already have
some sort of barrier on it,
and he's asking for a
little more than 200 miles,
so I think that puts it in perspective,
but he wants it to be put in positions
where drug trafficking, human trafficking,
and illegal immigration is happening
in the most severe manner right now.
- Do you see the Democrat,
from what you know,
we just heard Congressman Clyburn say
he believes there can be success
in that conference committee,
that left to their own devices
they can come up with an agreement?
Do you, are you optimistic
that's gonna happen as well?
- Well, I'm hopeful.
I'm not sure I'm optimistic yet,
but I'm very hopeful.
We'll know tomorrow, because
some experts from the border,
these are non-political bent people
who are coming up to give
some advice to the committee,
I'm hopeful tomorrow
we'll hear some statements
coming out of that conference committee
that'll give us some optimism
about getting past this impasse.
Look, the other thing, Judy,
is that this is ridiculous.
This is a appropriation
issue that should have
been dealt with before
September 30th of last year.
We're in the fifth month
of our new fiscal year,
so I'm hopeful that
everybody will sober up here
in Congress and get this done this week.
- I think you know,
Senator, the President is
still not ruling out the idea of
declaring a national emergency in order to
go ahead and build the wall,
put money aside to build the wall
if there's no agreement in Congress,
but he's been told by
Senate Majority Leader,
your colleague, Senator
McConnell, Mitch McConnell,
that that's not a good idea.
Do you think the President still
would seriously consider doing that?
- Well, he has said he
would and I take him
at his word, but, again, this is a man.
I think tonight in the State of the Union,
you'll hear President Trump offer a little
more conciliatory tone
because he's a dealmaker
first and last, we all know that.
He just wants to get border security
moving in the right direction
and both parties actually want that,
so I'm hopeful that tonight,
we'll see a little more of that
and then over the next week or so,
we'll see something come out
of this conference committee
that will preclude the
need for the President
to do something extreme like that.
He certainly has the right to do it,
but I'm hopeful Congress will
step in here and do its job.
- Senator, how much, how does it change
what the President can do because
Democrats have now won the majority
in the House of Representatives,
that he's dealing with
a different Congress
than he was last year?
- Well, we have a historic opportunity.
If you think about Tip O'Neill and Reagan,
you think about Newt
Gingrich and Bill Clinton,
when you had split government is when
really big things did happen here,
so the answer is, Nancy Pelosi
has a choice as the Speaker.
Either she's gonna work
with this President,
who's been proven that
he will make a deal.
I mean, we did a historic
bipartisan Dodd-Frank bill
just this past year, Judy,
that really helped small banks.
I'm looking for more of that,
so I think the Speaker
has to make a decision.
Is she gonna legislate
with this President,
who's more than willing to do that,
or is she just gonna investigate
going into the Presidential
election in 2020?
- But my question is how does it change
what the President is able to do?
- Well, if they don't operate with us,
then it moves back in the Senate,
and all we're gonna be
focused on are confirmations
and Leader McConnell has talked about
being more aggressive about getting
the confirmations done this year and next,
so we know we can do that.
That's in the hands of the Senate.
I just implore the Senate,
or the House members,
to put pressure on leadership there to,
let's get together and legislate,
which is why the people in
America sent us up here.
- There's a report out in
the last few days, Senator,
about the Trump administration still not
having submitted names for hundreds of
empty positions inside the administration.
Do you have an explanation
for why that is?
- Well, yeah.
We've had a historic level
of obstruction, first of all.
Let's put it.
- [Judy] No, I'm talk.
- No, I understand.
The good news is is
that we have done over,
we've confirmed over 85 judges,
30 Courts of Appeal judges,
and two Supreme Court Justices
because the party was set there,
but this is a historic situation, Judy,
where this is the first
time in U.S. history
the minority party has not waived
the 30-hour rule in the Senate.
Now, having said that, there are over
300 nominations at the end of last year
waiting to be confirmed.
We just need to get down to business
and get past this and stop
playing partisan politics.
This President is, if we
don't change the rule,
and we don't move past this,
this President won't even be able to
put his full complement of government
together in the first term of his office.
- Yeah, I'm asking about those positions
for which names have not
even put forward yet.
- Well, first of all, Judy,
there are plenty of names
that have been put
forward that have not been
brought forward because
we can't get to them
because of the obstruction of
the Democrats in the Senate,
and when that happens I can promise you
this President will
line 'em up in terms of
the nominees waiting to be confirmed.
- Senator David Perdue of
Georgia, thank you very much.
- Thanks, Judy.
- So, let's take a step back now
and put this moment in tonight's address
in context with Presidential historian
and NewsHour regular Michael Beschloss.
Michael Beschloss, wonderful to see you.
- Wonderful to see you always.
- Thank you for being here.
- Thank you, Judy.
- So, you've looked at how
Presidents have handled
times of stress, times when
they are facing opposition,
whether new or long-standing.
That seems to be, certainly,
what President Trump is facing tonight.
How have other Presidents handled it?
- Well, oftentimes they've made a pivot.
I mean, Bill Clinton, for instance,
in 1996 was about to run for reelection
and two years earlier,
he had lost Congress
to the Republicans,
first time in 40 years.
That was a very big event, so he said,
we remember it now, the era
of big government is over.
That worked for him because people knew
that for the year since the election,
he had been moving steadily to the right
or at least to the center,
so when he said those
words it had some meaning,
helped to position him to run
successfully for reelection
and also, I was so interested
that Senator Perdue
was talking about Newt
Gingrich and Bill Clinton.
That State of the Union set that up
for Clinton and Gingrich,
by the summer of 1996,
to do welfare reform together,
to balance the budget.
It really changed the
political atmosphere.
- So is there a precedent,
Michael Beschloss,
for Presidents who've been at loggerheads
with a Congress turning the corner
and setting the stage
for there to be real,
an ability to work together?
- Yeah, absolutely.
1947, Harry Truman went to
give the State of the Union
after he lost Congress to the Republicans
for the first time in 16 years.
He knew that there was
a big necessity for him
to make deals with the Republicans
to prepare the nation
to fight the Cold War
and to try to get some of the
domestic laws that he wanted.
He failed at the latter.
- Do you sense, again
from you studied history,
studied so many Presidents,
that there is a willingness,
a will, on the part of these two parties
that have been fighting each
other for week after week,
day after day, to come together?
- I think they know that an awful lot
of Americans would like to see that.
That surely shows up in the polls,
but there hasn't been much sign of it
during the last month and we will see if
this speech changes the atmosphere.
I think rarely in
history does that happen.
- And that's what I want
to ask you about, too.
How much difference can one speech, one,
granted this is a big deal,
it's the State of the Union.
There's a whole lot of
tradition wrapped around this.
- Sure.
- Can one address make a difference?
- If people have the feeling that lurking
within Donald Trump has
been this deep desire
to make deals with the other side
that hasn't expressed itself,
and he talked about it a
lot during the campaign.
2016, a lot of people
voted for Trump did so
because he said, I know Chuck Schumer,
I can make deals with him,
and they feel in many cases
that it hasn't been expressed,
if we begin to see signs
of that Donald Trump
in the wake of this speech,
things could begin to change.
I'm not predicting that.
- Are you, why not?
- Because this speech was preceded by an
enormous confrontation, one of the biggest
in legislative White
House relations history
that led to a shutdown, may yet again.
- And just very quickly, you've looked at
the language this President uses,
the way he communicates
with the American people.
Do you, how much do you expect
him to stay in that lane,
and how much might he?
- Not for long.
He doesn't enjoy it, we haven't
seen many instances of it.
If we did, the time we would have seen it
would have been in the inauguration
when even the most partisan Presidents
usually give a really unifying speech.
He'd be the first to say he did not.
- Michael Beschloss, thank you.
- My pleasure.
- Nice to have you.
Appreciate it.
And now, some perspective
on the run-up to tonight's
big address from opposite sides
of the American political spectrum.
Karine Jean-Pierre is a
senior advisor for MoveOn.org
and Chris Buskirk is the editor of the
conservative journal and
web site American Greatness.
Hello to both of you.
- Hi.
- Hi, Judy.
- Great to have you back on the program.
Chris, to you first, Chris Buskirk.
What do you expect the
President to do tonight?
- I think what the
President's gonna do tonight
is he is going to do what he's done,
I think pretty well in
some speeches before,
which he's going to go back to
promises made, promises kept.
Here's what I talked about in my campaign,
here's what I've accomplished so far,
here's what I still need to do,
and I think that, here we are halfway
through the first term, right.
This has got to be the
pivot to reelection,
so try to start to set the tone
and set the trajectory for a message
that's going to carry him
through November of 2020,
and I think that needs to
be one big unifying theme
that says, on immigration,
on trade, on foreign policy,
how are all these things linked together?
What's that unifying theme?
And I think that that theme has to be
how do you rebuild the middle
class, that's number one,
and I think that that's
what he's gonna try and do.
- And if that's what he
does, Karine Jean-Pierre,
how is that received by Democrats?
- So, I know that it's been reported that,
from the administration,
from the White House,
that the President is going
to give a speech on unity,
on greatness, on bipartisanship,
and that would be great
if he was able to do that,
but we haven't seen
that from this President
in the past, now going on three years,
and I just don't see the speech,
only because of his
history, of his record,
being that impactful, so
maybe, maybe he gets there
and he makes a unity speech,
but hours later, the
moment he gets on Twitter,
it all, he steps on it.
So, I just, it's hard to believe
and let's not forget, a couple weeks ago,
he gave, he addressed the country
in a diplomatic reception room
where he talked about immigration,
and that was filled with division,
and then he did it weeks prior to that
in the Oval Office
behind the Resolute desk
and that was filled
with division and hate,
so I just don't see how that's possible
coming from this President.
- And in fact, Chris Buskirk,
I had a chance today
to spend a little bit,
a few minutes with Speaker Pelosi
and the Senate Minority
Leader, Chuck Schumer,
and Mr. Schumer made a point,
Senator Schumer made a point of saying,
we hope the President's
going to appeal to unity,
but in the past, when
he's spoken at a moment
whether it's the State
of the Union address
or another speech, he's made promises
or made declarations that he then
turned around and didn't fulfill,
so what makes you convinced
that tonight is gonna be different?
- Well, I think part of that's
in the eye of the beholder, right.
What is unity?
I mean, there's part of it that is
the art of persuasion,
which is to talk about it
and to use the rhetoric of unity
and to talk about how do we,
how are we Americans together,
what does that mean and how
do we build things together,
make this a better society.
How that translates
into practice, I think,
is where the President
needs to be very concrete.
He needs to use that
rhetoric, but then say,
look, these are the
policies we're gonna pursue
in my administration to try
and make this a reality,
and that's what everybody's
really looking for.
It's nice to hear the good speech,
but then what are you gonna do about it?
- But you have a sense
that now, Chris Buskirk,
the President's prepared to do that?
- I think he has to, and I think that's
what he's gonna try and do.
- But, Karine,
(laughing)
you're expressing doubt.
- I, he just doesn't have
a record of it, Judy.
We have not seen that.
A year ago, he talked about unity.
What did we get months later?
We got the zero policy situation
where children were being
ripped away from their parents,
children of undocumented immigrants
coming through the southern border,
and that was devastating to see
and now we're hearing many of them
will never be reunited,
and the year before that, in 2017,
in the joint address, the same thing,
and what did we see?
We heard about Charlottesville
and what did he do there?
He said, very fine people on both sides.
I just don't see it.
- When you hear this, Chris Buskirk,
what do you think?
- I think that unity does not
mean agreement on everything
and that's okay, that's
what politics is for.
I think what unity means is
not that Donald Trump says,
well, to Speaker Pelosi,
okay whatever you want, that's fine.
I think what it means is how do we
identify the problems
that the country faces
and then how do we work together
where there's agreement
and then we can disagree
on other things too, but
let's do that in a way
where we at least try and set
the table on common goals.
- And I guess the flip
side of the question,
Karine Jean-Pierre, is are Democrats
or people like you who work
hard with organizations.
- Yeah.
- Who oppose so much of
the President's policies,
are you willing to give the President
the benefit of the doubt?
- There are things that we can work on
that's bipartisanship, which is DACA,
infrastructure, improving.
- [Judy] Which is immigration.
- Immigration, right, for
young undocumented folks
who came here with their parents
when they were really young
and there's also the
criminal justice, right?
That was done in a bipartisan way.
It was a first step, and
there's more to be done.
The problem is, and what we said earlier,
he declares things in his speech
but then he doesn't stick to them
and I think Democrats are ready
to work on those things I just mentioned,
but he doesn't stick to it.
- I want to look at this,
step back a little bit,
Chris Buskirk, because part
of what's going on here
is that many of the people
who support the President
don't seem to want him to cooperate
with the other side and Karine,
I think you could say that about
a number of progressive liberal Democrats
who don't want to see
their party cooperate.
What about that, Chris?
- Well, the best way for me,
at least, to think about it
is to use a concrete illustration.
So you think about the immigration issue.
I mean, this is a place where people like
Speaker Pelosi and
Minority Leader Schumer,
you know, 10 years ago, 12 years ago,
they were talking, yes we need a wall,
we need border security.
I think what the President needs to do
is explain why that's important
and how that is something that protects,
how border security
protects working families,
American working families.
Why, because it protects
their most valuable asset,
which is their asymmetric access
to the American labor market.
Make that argument, maybe in a more.
- [Judy] In other words,
immigrants take jobs away from you?
Is that, I mean?
- Take jobs away, lower wages.
I mean, more supply equals,
more supply lowers prices.
That's basic.
You explain that to people and say,
look, this is why
immigration's important to me,
or this is why trade
policy's important to me,
'cause I want middle income families
to be secure economically
and they to be able to prosper.
- And Karine, the flip side of that.
Liberal Democrats don't
want their party leaders
to work together with the President.
- Well, they want Democrats,
in particular in the House
now that it's the majority,
to hold this President accountable,
and that's one of the reasons
that we took back the House,
and so that's really important,
and that looks in very
different ways, right?
That's looking at this Mueller report.
That's also looking at, as I mentioned,
the children being
separated at the border,
Puerto Rico, 3,000 people died,
but they also want to see Democrats
moving the country forward, right,
and they've done that with voting rights
and dealing with corruption and so
those are things that
they actually want to see,
but we need Republicans
on the other side to do,
to also in there with us, too.
- All right, we're gonna have a chance
to talk about all this again later tonight
when we've heard what
the President has to say.
Thank you so much, Karine
Jean-Pierre, Chris Buskirk.
- Thank you.
(upbeat music)
- And now for a roundup of
today's other main headlines.
Here's Amna Nawaz.
- In the non-State of
the Union news today,
the White House played
down a federal subpoena
seeking a host of documents
from President Trump's
inaugural committee.
Federal prosecutors in
New York are investigating
who gave the money and what they
might have received in return.
White House spokeswoman
Sarah Sanders called it
"hysteria over the fact
that Mr. Trump was elected."
- This doesn't have anything
to do with the White House,
and I think the biggest focus
and the thing that most
Americans care about
has nothing to do with the inaugural
and it has everything to do
with what the path forward looks like.
- Investigators are also
looking into whether
any foreign donors illegally contributed
to the inaugural committee.
One of President Trump's judicial nominees
voiced regrets today
for her past statements
on rape, race, and equal rights.
Neomi Rao appeared before the
Senate Judiciary Committee.
Senators on both sides criticized her
for writing in college
that women bear some blame
if they're sexually
assaulted while intoxicated.
- To be honest, looking back
at some of those writings
and rereading them, I cringe at some
of the language that I used.
Now, I've had a lot of
experience since that time
writing in college, and
I don't think I would
express myself in the same way.
These are horrible crimes,
and I wouldn't write
anything that might be
implied to blame a victim or make it
less likely for a victim to come forward.
- Rao currently leads
the White House office
overseeing deregulation.
If confirmed, she'd take the
federal Appeals Court seat
held by Brett Kavanaugh before
he joined the Supreme Court.
Overseas, in Afghanistan,
Taliban attacks killed
nearly 50 people in
two northern provinces.
A pre-dawn raid killed
26 soldiers and police
at an army base in Kunduz province,
on the outskirts of Kunduz City.
Attacks in neighboring
provinces killed 21 others.
The Taliban have kept up their offensive,
even amid early stages of
peace talks with the U.S.
The top U.S. commander
in the Middle East says
President Trump did not talk to him
before announcing American
forces will withdraw from Syria.
Army General Joseph Votel testified
at a Senate hearing
today and was questioned
by Maine Senator Angus King.
- General, were you aware
of the President's intention
to order the withdrawal
of our troops from Syria
before that was publicly announced?
- I was not aware of the
specific announcement.
Certainly we are aware that
he had expressed a desire
and intent in the past to
depart Iraq, er, I meant Syria.
- So you weren't consulted
before that decision was announced?
- [Votel] We were not,
I was not consulted.
- Votel's remarks came a day after
the Defense Department warned that
Islamic State fighters could resurge
in Syria after the U.S. withdraws,
and this afternoon the Senate approved
a Middle East security bill that warns
against any sudden pullout
from Syria or Afghanistan.
It also calls for new sanctions on Syria.
Pope Francis has celebrated the first ever
Papal mass on the Arabian peninsula.
Some 180,000 people gathered today
at a sports stadium in Abu Dhabi,
capital of the United Arab Emirates.
Francis preached humility
in one of the world's richest nations.
(speaking foreign language)
- [Papal Translator] For
Jesus on the other hand,
blessed are the poor, the meek,
those who remain just, even at the cost
of appearing in a bad light,
those who are persecuted.
He taught us that greatness
is not found in having
but rather in giving.
- Later, the Pope acknowledged,
for the first time,
the scandal of priests
sexually abusing nuns.
He said he's committed
to fighting the problem.
Millions of people, meanwhile,
in Asia and around the world
marked the Lunar New Year today.
In Taiwan, thousands gathered
to pray at a Buddhist temple.
In the Philippines,
people bought roasted pig,
a delicacy, to usher
in the Year of the Pig,
and all across China,
crowds visited temples
and took part in festivals.
Back in this country, Texas lawmakers
complained today the state
still has not received
Hurricane Harvey recovery funds.
The storm did major damage
in 2017 and last February,
Congress earmarked some
$4.4 billion for Texas,
but no grants have actually been made.
The state's Republican
senators plus 10 House members
from both parties say
federal budget bureaucracy
is what's standing in the way.
An outspoken critic of the
World Bank, David Malpass,
looks like he'll be President Trump's
choice to lead the agency.
It was widely reported today that
the President will nominate him this week.
The World Bank provides loans
and projects around the world,
but Malpass has complained it's
piling up debt without results.
Also today, Andrew Wheeler won
a Senate Committee's approval
to be head of the EPA.
His nomination now goes
to the full Senate,
and on Wall Street, a series
of strong earnings reports
gave stocks another boost.
The Dow Jones industrial
average gained 172 points
to close at 25,411.
The NASDAQ rose 54 points,
and the S&P 500 added 12.
Still to come on the NewsHour,
reaction to the President's comments
that the U.S. will use a base in Iraq
to keep eyes on Iran.
A rigorous program prepares
Black undergraduates
to go on to medical school.
Plus, SAS Rachel Kaadzi Ghansah gives her
brief but spectacular
take on fearlessness.
(upbeat music)
- As we reported, the top
U.S. military commander
for the Middle East was
on Capitol Hill today.
In addition to the fight against ISIS,
he was asked about recent
comments by President Trump
suggesting American troops in Iraq
could shift their mission,
and as Nick Schifrin reports,
those comments about
U.S. troops watching Iran
have sparked deep concern in Iraq.
- [Schifrin] Near the Iraqi-Syrian border,
(yelling in foreign language)
an Iraqi soldier and his American advisor
line up artillery to strike ISIS.
(mortar firing)
Outside Baghdad, U.S.
Special Operations forces
train Iraq's elite
counterterrorism service,
(gun rapidly firing)
and Iraqi soldiers learn
to fire American rifles
from anti-ISIS coalition troops.
These scenes of partnership,
filmed by the U.S. military
over the past year,
show what Iraq has invited the U.S. to do.
- [Soldier] Fire!
(gun booming)
- [Schifren] 5,200 troops
train Iraqi security forces
and target ISIS fighters
who lost territory
but resumed insurgent tactics,
but this weekend, President Trump
told CBS's Margaret Brennan
the mission should expand.
- And one of the reasons I want to keep it
is because I want to be
looking a little bit at Iran,
because Iran is a real problem.
- Whoa, that's news.
You're keeping troops in Iraq
because you want to be
able to strike in Iran?
- No, because I want to
be able to watch Iran.
All I want to do is be able to watch.
- [Schifren] But even watching Iran
exceeds the tasks Iraq has approved.
Today Iraqi Prime
Minister Adil Abdul-Mahdi,
who has been working
with the United States,
criticized President Trump.
(speaking foreign language)
- [Iraqi Translator] I don't think
that such statements are useful.
In fact, they won't help much
and I hope that he would
back down from them.
- [Schifren] In a statement,
First Deputy Speaker
Hassan al-Kaabi repeated a vow
that Parliament would pass a law
"terminating the security
agreement with America,
"in addition to ending the presence
"of American military
trainers and advisors
"and foreigners on Iraqi soil,"
(speaking foreign language)
and on a Lebanon-based
TV network on Sunday,
Iranian-backed militia
spokesman Jaafar al-Husseini
hinted militias had the
capacity to evict the U.S.
(speaking foreign language)
- [Iranian Translator] All of our options
are open in front of us.
We have the ability and
resources to execute them.
- What the President's remarks have done
is to make it more difficult for
even America's closest allies
and the Iraqi political class
to continue to advocate for
the American presence in Iraq.
- [Schifren] Feisal Istrabadi
is a former Iraqi diplomat
and directs Indiana University's Center
for the Study of the Middle East.
The Iraqi Parliament was
already debating a bill
that would evict the U.S.
That momentum will
increase and put pressure
on Prime Minister Adil Abdul-Mahdi,
who leads a government
considered technically capable
but has no natural constituency.
- He was turned to by the
political parties in Parliament
and asked to form a government.
He is in that sense a
relatively weak Prime Minister
and you don't want the Prime Minister
in a political battle with Parliament
because in the Iraqi system,
the Prime Minister will always lose.
- [Schifren] Today the top
commander in the Middle East,
General Joseph Votel, tried
to reassure that the U.S.
Respected Iraqi wishes.
- Our military mission on the ground
remains very focused on the reason
that the government of Iraq
asked us to come there.
- [Schiffren] And he suggested
the President's comments
had not become a military order.
Virginia Democrat Senator Tim Kaine.
- And as far as you know,
there is not a change in the
definition of the mission,
at least as far as the
Pentagon is concerned?
- I have no additional tasks that have
been given to me with regard to that.
- If the U.S. were to
change its definition
of the mission in Iraq to be a mission
about watching Iran, wouldn't
it be pretty important
to have Iraq agree that that would be
the focus of the mission if we were
to be having troops in their country
to carry out such a mission?
- Senator, we are in
Iraq at the invitation
of the government, so yes I agree.
- I think that this
statement is not enough.
- [Schiffren] Abbas Kadhim
leads the Atlantic Council's
Iraq Initiative and recently
met with President Salih.
Kadhim says thanks to
President Trump's statement,
Iran's powerful allies can
now use the Iraqi constitution
to argue against U.S. presence,
because it requires Iraq to
"adhere to the principle
of noninterference
"in the internal affairs of other states."
- Iran has more friends
inside Iraqi Parliament,
and also inside the government
and inside even the public
and these friends are
willing to indulge Iran.
Before Sunday, they
did not have the votes.
Now I am told by some Parliament members
that they have the votes at least
to have it pass through the first reading.
That is a major shift.
(rotors whirring)
- [Schiffren] Iraqi leaders admit
they knew all along U.S. troops in Iraq
were likely conducting extra missions,
even watching Iran, but until Sunday
that was never made public.
- That veil of plausible deniability
or willful ignorance,
whatever you want to call it,
that's been lifted.
The President of the United States
has blatantly announced
what his agenda actually is.
- [Schiffren] And that means,
for the U.S. and Iraqi
officials whose agenda
is to improve Iraq, their
mission became much harder.
(gun firing)
For the PBS NewsHour, I'm Nick Schiffren.
(upbeat music)
While Virginia's governor Ralph Northam
weighs whether to resign,
reaction and anger keeps building
over the racist photo in
his medical school yearbook.
One important part of
that is how it serves
as a reminder of racism
in medicine historically.
We reported on the importance of training
more African-Americans to become doctors,
and tonight we have a second look
at a story on Xavier University.
It's a small, historically Black college
in New Orleans that's
helping lead the way.
Hari Sreenivasan reports on
what sets the school apart
for our education
series, Making the Grade.
- Can any of y'all come up to the board
and describe the glycolysis
cycle, like write it out?
- [Sreenivasan] On the
campus of Xavier University,
18-year old Chris Webb
leads a biology review
the night before a major test.
- All you really need to know.
- [Sreenivasan] Webb is
helping fellow freshmen who,
like him, are enrolled in a
rigorous pre-medical program.
- I want them to do as best as they can.
- [Sreenivasan] The
scene is a familiar one
on the campus of Xavier, a
historically Black college
in the heart of New Orleans.
- So what's the second stage
in aerobic respiration?
- The second stage is
formation of acetyl coenzyme A.
- Okay.
- [Sreenivasan] Students
quiz each other on material
from tough science classes,
the kind of courses
that often weed out pre-medical students.
- I don't want them to do better than me,
but when they do, that
just makes me realize,
okay this competition is really serious.
While we're having fun,
it's also very real.
- There are just over 3,000
students at Xavier University,
but the school manages to
graduate more African-Americans
who go on to become doctors
than any other school.
That includes elite public universities
and the Ivy Leagues.
That number is even more striking
given a drop in Black males
applying to medical schools.
According to a recent report from the
Association of American Medical Colleges,
fewer Black males are applying to
medical schools now than in 1978.
Reynold Verret, Xavier's president.
- We do not compete to say who's better.
It's almost like a relay race.
The goal is to finish together,
so our students actually embrace
and encourage each other to achieve.
- That turns on its head
traditional pre-med programs.
- Oh yes, it does.
- Which is look to the
left, look to the right.
- One of you's gone.
- [Sreenivasan] Right?
- Yes.
We want to get through
because the competition
is actually after we
leave Xavier, not here.
The point is to get out there together.
- [Student] Glucose make two.
- [Sreenivasan] Call it
competitive collaboration.
Head of student advising
Quo Vadis Webster.
- At some schools, you say
look to your left, look to your right,
this person may not be here.
Here, we say look to your
left, look to your right,
you better help the person next to you
so that we can all make it.
- [Sreenivasan] The intense
student advising starts early.
- How are you, my dear?
- [Student] I'm great, how are you?
- Good, everything is filled out?
- [Sreenivasan] Incoming freshmen begin
crafting medical school applications,
even before their first
day as an undergraduate.
- Before classes start, we
go over a different aspect
of the process of preparing a competitive
application to medical school.
- And you're starting before
they actually walk in the door?
- Have to.
You need six semesters at least,
'cause that's six
semesters before you apply.
You need every last one of
those semesters and summers
to put into making yourself
a competitive applicant.
- One of the phosphates is broken off.
- [Sreenivasan] The
pre-med program also relies
heavily on tutoring by upperclassmen.
Bradley Dunn says he
could not have made it
through his first semester
without the free tutoring center.
Dunn's student tutor, Chinyere Jones.
- Basically, whenever he had a break,
he was in the tutoring center.
I was like, geez.
- [Sreenivasan] Dunn believes
students helping students
comes in part from shared
experiences about race.
- They're able to understand
the plight of African-Americans.
It's more relatable
and it's more intimate,
and we all know the pitfalls
that we may face as people,
and together we're a unit,
and I'm actually taking
pride in that blackness.
- The second part of that question,
that's the one I didn't
necessarily understand.
- [Sreenivasan] Race is
also an important factor
for Chris Webb, who chose
Xavier over full scholarships
to other universities including
Vanderbilt and Tulane.
- Seeing people that looked like me
and getting to med school
and through med school,
it motivates me more competing
with people that are like me.
- [Sreenivasan] One of those role models
is Dr. Ryan Jupiter.
- All right, if you don't mind,
I'm gonna take a listen to you right now.
- [Sreenivasan] Jupiter
is a resident doctor
in the emergency department of
New Orleans University Medical Center.
A Xavier alumni, he
visits campus regularly
to tell students his own story
as the first in his
family to go to college.
- I wanted to make sure
that I could look like I do
and still be able to
become what I want to be.
- [Sreenivasan] How important is that?
I mean, do you think that young black men
don't see that enough?
- Definitely, I don't
think they do at all.
It's a long journey, and
when you see other people
who put in the time and the work
and see the results of it,
then it kinda helps with the
long struggle that it takes.
- [Sreenivasan] When we met Dr. Jupiter,
he had his monogrammed jacket on,
which he took off for our interview,
but he explained how he normally wears
the jacket in the hospital because
it is one more visual cue to patients
that he is a physician,
something he says people
don't always expect
from a young black male.
- [Sreenivasan] Have you been mistaken
for something other than a doctor?
- All the time.
(laughing)
It happens.
I don't think it's intentional.
I would like to think
it's not intentional,
but it's very rare that
you can walk into a room
as a patient and when you see
a Black, African-American
male with dreads in his hair,
that this is my doctor until you
formally introduce yourself,
or you will get the comments.
Nurse, or can you get this for me,
or are you here to clean
the room, so to speak,
those things have all happened.
- [Sreenivasan] Students at Xavier hope
to change those stereotypes.
- We all recognize that
people don't truly see us
for who we are, and we use that
to motivate ourselves and
to try to show people,
we're a lot more than
what you take us for.
- As African-Americans, we're
known to be great at sports,
but we can be so much
greater in other areas,
and I just feel like we
need to be more represented.
(jazzy music)
- [Sreenivasan] There's a bright spot
for minority trends in the field.
The number of Black women applying
to medical school is on the rise.
- Black women have something to prove.
- [Sreenivasan] Xavier
sophomore Rachel Hitchens
has already been accepted into the
University of Rochester medical school.
- We've been objectified
for so many years.
We have to prove that we can
be more than video dancers.
We can actually use our brain,
and I think that is,
that's the motivating force
that's deep down within so
many Black women like myself.
- [Sreenivasan] And like
Hitchens, the students we spoke to
at this small New Orleans
college had big plans.
- I want to be an orthopedic surgeon.
- I want to be a pediatric cardiologist.
- I want to be a rural
family practice physician.
- [Sreenivasan] Paving the
way for another generation
of African-American doctors.
In New Orleans, for the PBS NewsHour,
I'm Hari Sreenivasan.
(upbeat music)
- Finally tonight, a
generous journalism prize
was awarded by the
Heising Simons Foundation.
The American Mosaic Prize is given
to two freelance journalists
for long-form reporting
that highlights underrepresented groups
in the American landscape.
The two recipients this
year are Abe Streep
and Rachel Kaadzi Ghansah, whose work
also received the
Pulitzer Prize last year.
Ghansah was featured in our
Brief but Spectacular series
in 2016, and so we
bring that to you again,
and we congratulate her and
Abe Streep for this honor
with encouragement to continue
doing meaningful journalism.
- I like writing about
people who look like me
and the people I know who don't
have good pieces written about them,
because we deserve it.
(clapping)
(serious music)
I've written about Jimi
Hendrix, Electric Lady Studios,
Toni Morrison,
Kendrick Lamar,
the Watts riots,
Trayvon Martin,
Rachel Jeantel,
Dave Chappelle.
We don't always hear about the people
who we know as legends, the ways that
they were very true to themselves.
I'm more interested in the moments
when they were uncompromising
and they were fearless because what I hope
is that that fearlessness tells us
a little bit about how we can be fearless.
What was interesting to
me about Dave Chappelle
was that here's a moment where
typically walking away
from Comedy Central,
walking away from your career
would be a bad decision,
and anyone would tell you don't do that.
The common understanding
of it is is that he felt
that the show had
started to cross the line
and that it was actually becoming
a source of embarrassment,
and so walking away from $50 million
was pretty heroic and pretty
decent and full of integrity.
Well, you know, I couldn't
read until I was 12.
Maybe I wasn't 12, but I was older.
I think people start reading
when they're five or something,
and so books were kind of
this phantasmagorical space
that I couldn't enter
because my mom could read,
my dad was an academic,
everyone was so intelligent,
and I couldn't go there,
and the moment I could,
I just started to read ravenously.
One of the books that I remember
changing everyone's lives was Beloved.
That was the first time
people who had been silenced,
enslaved people became
human, and at that moment
I said, this is what a
writer can do and so for me,
Toni Morrison doesn't
exist on a human plane.
She almost exists in this
odd, spiritual other world
in terms of her work, and
when she won that Nobel Prize,
what was interesting is that
a lot of prominent newspapers asked,
does this woman deserve it?
So when I had the moment to take
the New York Times Magazine cover,
I decided I'm gonna take that cover
to lay flowers at the feet of this woman
and say not only did you
deserve it, but thank you.
My name is Rachel Kaadzi Ghansah,
and this is my brief but spectacular take
on fearlessness and black art.
- Congratulations again,
and you can catch up
on other Brief but Spectacular episodes
on our website, pbs.org/newshour/brief,
and a reminder, join us
tonight at nine pm Eastern
for special coverage of President Trump's
State of the Union address
and the Democratic Party response.
We'll be carrying both
speeches live on air and online
at pbs.org/newshour, along with
analysis and fact-checking.
Plus, you'll want to listen to a special
State of the Union episode of our podcast
with insights and conversation
you won't get anywhere else.
Listen to this special
episode when you subscribe
to any of our PBS NewsHour podcasts,
which are available on our web site
at pbs.org/newshour/podcasts,
or wherever you like to listen,
and that's the NewsHour for now.
I'm Judy Woodruff.
For all of us at the PBS NewsHour,
thank you and we'll be
back at nine pm Eastern.
(serious music)
- [Announcer] Major funding
for the PBS NewsHour
has been provided by:
- [Narrator] Babbel, a language program
that teaches Spanish, French,
Italian, German, and more.
- [Announcer] Consumer Cellular.
American Cruise Lines.
BNSF Railway.
The Ford Foundation,
working with visionaries
on the front lines of
social change worldwide.
Carnegie Corporation of New York,
supporting innovations and education,
democratic engagement, and the advancement
of international peace and
security, at carnegie.org,
and with the ongoing support of
these individuals and institutions.
(serious music)
This program was made possible
by the Corporation for Public Broadcasting
and by contributions to your PBS station
from viewers like you.
Thank you.
(serious music)
- [Narrator] You're watching PBS.
(ringing)
- [Announcer] Celebrities
take an emotional trip
through their ancestry, filled
with secrets and surprises.
A new season of Finding
Your Roots is next on TV26.
- [Trump] This is national
security we're talking about.
We're not talking about games.
- [Pelosi] We're not doing a wall.
Let there not be any doubt
that we're not doing a wall.
(bell ringing)
- [Trump] They're incredible job numbers,
beyond anybody's expectation.
- [Announcer] Live coverage of the
State of the Union
address, tonight at nine.
- [Narrator] Vast, frozen,
this is no place to be a lone wolf.
Here, prey are fierce
and five times your size.
To succeed, you need family,
because in the Arctic,
strength in numbers is
the only way to survive.
(wolf howling)
- [Announcer] Wednesday at eight on TV26.
- [Narrator] The mysteries
of Egypt's great pyramid.
- We need to know about
the people who built them.
Where's their settlement?
- [Narrator] Now, stunning discoveries.
- There's a void right through this wall.
- [Narrator] Are decoding
the great pyramid.
(rock clinking)
On Nova.
- [Announcer] Wednesday at nine on TV26.
- Franco had an idea
of the authentic Spain.
All of these things were
challenged by the left.
- Franco believed that he should eliminate
the left and their ideology.
- [Historian] Franco never
lost a minute's sleep
over the crimes that were
committed in his name.
- [Announcer] Wednesday at 10 on TV26.
(celestial music)
- Won't you be my neighbor?
It's an invitation to help somebody new.
That was at the root of everything.
Love or the lack of it.
Thank you for whatever you do
to bring joy and hope, light
and love, to our world today.
♪ Won't you please ♪
♪ Please won't you be my neighbor ♪
- [Announcer] Saturday at eight on TV26.
- [Narrator] Today's
programming is presented
by WETA members and the following:
(serious music)
- I was able to turn the aircraft around
and the mission around
and was able to save
two men's lives that night.
- My first job helped me
to grow up pretty quickly.
That'll happen when you're
asked to respond to a coup.
- In 2001, I signed up for the Air Force.
Two days later, 9/11 happened.
(serious music)
(energetic music)
[Narrator] Tonight, a new season
of Finding Your Roots at eight.
Then join the NewsHour for live coverage
of President Trump's State
of the Union address.
That's followed by Christiane
Amanpour, tonight on TV26,
(whooshing)
and on our WETA UK channel,
Doctor Blake and Doc Martin,
then, she ruled the UK for decades.
Don't miss a new season of Victoria.
British television at its best.
(light music)
- I'm Henry Louis Gates, Jr.
Welcome.