(enthusiastic flourishing)
- It seems that television
has become a kind
of electronic confessional.
- It is juicy, newsy, exciting stuff.
- What are we doing here?
Why did we start this business?
- Any tool for human
expression will bring out both
the best and the worst of us
and television has been there.
- [Announcer] Here's
Michael at the foul line.
A shot on Ehlo, good!
- They don't pay me enough to
deal with animals like this.
(laughing)
- Why don't you just
get off my back, okay?
- People are no longer
embarrassed to admit
they watch television.
- Hello.
- People used to say, I was there.
Now they say they watch it on television.
(dramatic music)
(crowd cheering)
- [Dick] Slowly but surely,
the 1970s are disappearing.
The 1980s will be upon us.
What a decade it is coming up.
(crowd cheering)
Happy New Year!
- As you begin the 80s,
in the television world,
the landscape was, on any given evening,
nine out of 10 people were watching
only one of three networks.
- More than 30 million
people are addicted toit.
Social critics are
mystified by its success.
What is it?
It's television's prime time
prairie pot boiler, Dallas.
- A move like that'll
destroy all of Ewing Oil
and it'll ruin our family name.
- I assure you, a thought like
that never crossed my mind.
- Brother or no brother,
whatever it takes,
I'll stop you from destroying Ewing Oil.
- Dallas really did establish new ground
in terms of a weekly, one
hour show that literally
captivated America for 13 years.
- Dallas is a television
show which, in some ways,
is rooted in the 1970s,
and one of the crazy things
that emerges is this character, JR Ewing,
as a pop phenomenon.
- Tell me, JR, which slut are you going
to stay with tonight?
- What difference does it make?
Whoever it is has got be more interesting
than the slut I'm looking at right now.
- He was such a delicious villain.
Everyone was completely
enamored by this character.
- At this point, so many
people were watching television
that you could do something so unexpected
that it would become news overnight.
- Who's there?
(dramatic music)
(gun banging)
- The national obsession
in 1980 around who shot JR,
it's hard to imagine how obsessed
we all were with that question.
But we were.
- Who shot JR is about
as ideal a cliffhanger
as you possibly could get.
- Who did shoot JR?
We may never get that question.
The people who produce
that program are gonna keep
us in suspense for as
long as they possibly can.
- We shot JR and then
we broke for the summer.
Then, coincidentally,
the actors went on strike
and it delayed the resolution
and it just started
to percolate through the world.
- I remember going on vacation
to England that summer
and that's all that people
were talking about there.
- [Jessica] We know you don't die.
You couldn't die.
- Well, we don't know that.
- [Jessica] Well, how could you die?
You couldn't come back next season.
- That's what I mean.
I couldn't come back, but
the show could still go.
- [Jessica] Oh, but you wouldn't.
What is that show without JR?
- Well, that's what I figure!
- Well, I guess if you don't know by now
who shot JR, you probably do not care.
But last night, some 82
million Americans did
and they watched the much
touted Dallas episode.
It could become the most
watched television show ever.
(gun banging)
- Who shot JR is a reflection
of old fashioned television.
It's a moment that
gathers everybody around
the electronic fireplace which
is now the television set.
- Now, about one special
American television program,
a critic said, "It
transcends in popularity
"every other American
statement about war."
And something special happened today
to mobile Army Surgical Hospital 4077 that
will touch millions of Americans.
- It was the kind of event that
would draw the world's breath.
Stage nine, 20th Century Fox Studios,
the end of the Korean War,
the television version, MASH.
- It's been an honor and
a privilege to have worked
with you and I'm very, very
proud to have known you.
(dramatic music)
- There were those
landmark times when shows
that had been watched through the '70s
and into the '80s, like MASH,
had its final episode and we
were all sad to see them go.
- I'll miss you.
- I'll miss you, a lot.
(dramatic music)
- [Reporter] All over the
country, armies of fans crowded
around television sets to
watch the final episode
and to bid MASH farewell.
- The finale of MASH was unprecedented.
123 million people
watched one television
program at the same time.
- You know, I really should
be allowed to go home.
There's nothing wrong with me.
- When we ended the show,
we got telegrams of congratulations
from Henry Kissinger and Ronald Reagan.
The size of the response
and the emotional nature
of the response that we were getting
was difficult for us to understand.
- Who shot JR and the last episode of MASH
are the last call for the
pre-cable world of television.
It's like they are the last
time that that huge audience
will all turn up for one event.
(chopper blades whirring)
- TV is growing up with cable.
TV is growing up with content.
TV is growing up with different genres.
- The fundamental thing that cable did,
the VCR did, or the remote control did is
it gave consumers more choice
and everything was about to change.
(dramatic music)
- Dear Lexus.
- It is with a very grateful
heart that I write to you
about your amazing employees.
- [Male voiceover] Eric
volunteered to come
to my rescue that evening.
- [Female voiceover] To a mom,
these things really matter.
- [Male voiceover] From this day forward,
I'm a Lexus customer for life.
Thank you.
Sincerely--
- Ivy.
- Kim.
- David.
- Greg.
- Crafting every experience
for our guests with the same level
of care we craft our vehicles.
That's what makes Lexus Lexus.
Experience amazing at your Lexus dealer.
- Budget meeting!
- Sweet!
- If you compare last
quarter to this quarter--
- [All] Mmm.
- [Announcer] It's no
wonder everything seems
a little better with the
creamy taste of Philly,
made with fresh milk and real cream.
It must be the Philly.
- The cells in your body work in harmony.
Like you, they get hungry.
Feed them with new Centrum Multi Gummies,
specially crafted for men
and women, 50 and over,
so you're ready for anything.
Centrum, feed your cells today.
- With tough food, your
dentures may slip and fall.
Fixodent Ultra Max Hold gives you
the strongest hold ever
to lock your dentures.
So now you can eat tough
food without worry.
(lively music)
Fixodent and forget it.
- 145 over 92.
- 180 over 111.
- I had a heart attack, a cardiac
arrest, and then a stroke.
- [Announcer] This is what
high blood pressure looks like.
You might not feel its symptoms,
but the results from a
heart attack or stroke
are far from invisible or silent.
Get back on your plan
or talk with your doctor
to create an exercise,
diet and medication plan
that works for you.
Go to LowerYourHBP.org.
- If I would have
followed a treatment plan,
I would not be in this situation.
- [Announcer] Do you have an idea for
an invention or new product?
Do you think companies would
be interested in your idea?
Do you wanna try to get a patent?
Call InventHelp now for free information.
Call 1-800-492-4211.
- [Announcer] Take Prilosec OTC
and take control of heartburn,
so you don't have to stash antacids here.
Here.
Or here.
Kick your antacid habit with Prilosec OTC.
One pill a day, 24 hours, zero heartburn.
- Summer's not the time
for making bucket lists.
Bookers know summer is for booking it.
(bell ringing)
Like booking a beach
side resort and ordering
two more tacos than you need to, check.
Showing the deep end who's boss, check.
Starting a scooter gang
with the fam, check.
- Awesome.
- [Announcer] Bookers know
summer won't last forever.
- You're gonna thank me.
- [Announcer] So be a
booker at Booking.com,
the word's number one choice
for booking accommodations.
(lively music)
- Discover new San Pellegrino Essenza,
a twist of Mediterranean flavors
with the gentle bubbles of San Pellegrino.
Add a twist of flavor.
San Pellegrino Essenza,
tastefully Italian.
(dramatic music)
(goat bleating)
- Thomas Magnum?
- Marion Hammond?
- The private investigator?
- You're probably
wondering about the goat?
Just let me drop off my
friend and then we'll talk.
- When we entered the 80s,
a lot of one hour dramas
that were light hearted like Magnum PI
were very popular.
(tires squealing)
- After MASH went off
the air, the next season,
there wasn't a single
sitcom in the top 10.
First time that had ever
happened in TV history.
- The prevailing feeling was
that the sitcom was dead.
- [Jeff] Brandon Tartikoff,
NBC programming chief says,
reports of the sitcom's death
were greatly exaggerated.
- Time and time again, if
you study television history,
just when someone is counting a form out,
that is exactly the form of programming
that leads to the next big hit.
(lively music)
- So 1984, The Cosby Show comes on.
Now, Bill Cosby's not new to TV.
He's had other TV shows,
but The Cosby Show is very different.
It stands apart from
everything else he's done.
- Mom, I wanted my eggs scrambled.
- Coming right up.
(audience laughing)
- They talked about parenting.
Previous to that, on television,
the kids were cool and
the parents were idiots.
And then Cosby says the
parents are in charge
and that was something new.
- Instead of acting disappointed,
because I'm not like you,
maybe you can just accept
who I am and love me anyway,
because I'm your son.
(audience applauding)
- That's the dumbest thing
I've ever heard in my life.
- It helps the casting
of anything helps a lot
in television and the
kids were just great.
- If you were the last
person on this earth,
I still wouldn't tell you.
(audience laughing)
- You don't have to tell me what you did,
just tell me what they're gonna do to you.
((audience laughing)
- Unlike every other show on TV,
it's showing an upper
middle class black family.
And this wasn't All In The Family.
They weren't tackling deep
issues, but that was okay.
The mere fact that they
existed was a deep issue.
- The decade was waiting for
something real, in other words,
unless it's real, it doesn't
seem like it moves anybody.
If someone's feeling something,
you get to the heart, you get to the mind.
And if you can hit the hearts and minds,
you've got yourself a hit.
- How was school?
- School, dear, I
brought home two children
that may or may not be ours.
(audience laughing)
- Cosby Show brought this
tremendous audience to NBC
and that was a bridge to us.
Our ratings went way up.
♪ Sometimes you wanna go ♪
♪ Where everybody knows your name ♪
- Even the theme song to
Cheers put you in a good mood.
- Evenin' everybody.
- [All] Norm!
- Norman.
- What's shaking, Norm?
- All four cheeks and a
couple of chins, Coach.
(audience laughing)
- By the end of the Cheers pilot,
not only did you know who everybody was,
but you wanted to come back
and see what was gonna happen.
It's like all you have
to do is watch it once,
you're gonna love these people.
These are universal
characters and the humor
worked on so many levels.
- Last night, I was up
'til two in the morning
finishing off Kierkegaard.
- I hope he thanked you for it.
(audience laughing)
- You have to create a
community that people
are identifying with and Cheers
gives you that community.
- Boy I tell ya, I've
always wanted to sky dive,
I've just never had the guts.
What'd it feel like?
- Well, I imagine it's a lot like sex, ay.
Well, not that I have to
imagine what sex is like.
(audience laughing)
But I have plenty of sex.
I have plenty of this, too.
(audience laughing)
Why don't you just get off my back, okay.
- In the first episode,
there was a rather passionate annoyance.
I was saying, uh,
something's going on here.
A really intelligent woman
would see your line of BS a mile away.
- I've never met an intelligent
woman that I'd wanna date.
- On behalf of the intelligent
women around the world,
may I just say, phew.
(audience laughing)
- When we saw what Ted
and Shelley had together,
we said, oh no, you gotta
do this relationship.
- Ted and I understood what
they were writing right away.
- If you'll admit that you are carrying
a little torch for me, (audience laughing)
I'll admit that I'm carrying
a little one for you.
- Well, I am carrying
a little torch for you.
- Well, I'm not carrying one for you.
(audience laughing)
Diane knew how to tease Sam,
Sam knew how to tease Diane,
and I guess we knew how
to tease the audience.
(hands slapping)
(audience laughing)
- This incredible
chemistry between the two
of them ignited the show
and that's what drove
the show for the first five years.
- What the matter?
- Oh, I'm devastated.
I need something expeditious and brutal
to numb my sensibilities.
Blast me into sweet oblivion.
(audience laughing)
- How about a boilermaker?
- Make it a mimosa.
(audience laughing)
- We had the luck to be
able to rotate the cast
and every time we put somebody in,
there were explosions.
- Bwoah.
(audience laughing)
- There was something very
special about that setting,
those characters, that I never
got tired of writing that show.
- Sophisticated surveys,
telephonic samplings,
test audiences; all of those
things help to separate winners
from losers and make
mid-course corrections.
But you can't cut all comedies
from the same cookie cutters.
All you can hope is that every night
turns out like Thursday.
- Yo, Angela!
- Larry, Larry.
- Next. (gavel banging)
- How rude!
(audience laughing)
(cat meowing loudly)
- He's quick, I'll give him that.
- All of television said, oh,
well, maybe the sitcoms are alive again.
And that's all that it
took, it took one success.
- A few years from now,
something new may tempt
the people who pick what we see,
but it's a very safe guess that whatever
gets hot for a season or two,
the men and women who create
good television comedy
will be laughing all the way to the bank.
(dramatic music)
(lively music)
♪ Summer nights ♪
♪ Keeping me up ♪
♪ I wanna waste time ♪
♪ Just looking up the sky ♪
♪ Full of stars ♪
♪ Mind wandering far ♪
♪ Like we're 16, dreamin' in the dark ♪
♪ Love the wind in my hair ♪
♪ As I drive my car ♪
- [Announcer] Right now,
lease the Infiniti QX50
for $379 a month plus get
a $1,000 summer bonus now
during the Infiniti + summer sales event.
- My mom washes the dishes
before she puts them in the dishwasher.
So, what does the dishwasher do?
- [Announcer] Cascade Platinum
does the work for you,
pre-washing and removing
stuck on foods the first time.
- Wow, that's clean!
- [Announcer] Cascade Platinum.
- Wow, we did it.
We built the fastest network
for the latest iPhone.
- An iPhone 10R with the retina display
that makes everything look incredible.
- It's like the perfect couple, you know,
the ones who look great in every picture.
- Like the ones who always make
me feel like a before photo.
- [Both] Zoe and Chris.
- [Both] Hey, guys.
- Hey, Zoe and Chris.
How fun is that?
- Yeah.
- [Announcer] AT&T has the fastest network
for the latest iPhone.
Get the mind-blowing iPhone 10R on us
when you buy the latest iPhone.
AT&T, more for your thing.
That's our thing.
(dog howling)
- Dogs have evolved,
but their nutritional
needs remain instinctual.
That's why there's
Purina One True Instinct,
high protein for strong muscles,
a different breed of natural nutrition,
Purina One True Instinct.
Also in grain-free for dogs and cats.
- [Announcer] What if I wanted a margarita
without the guilt?
New Cape Line sparkling cocktails,
all the flavor with 75% less calories
than a classic margarita
and nothing artificial.
Welcome to Cape Line.
- Cake in the conference room.
- [Announcer] Showing 'em you're
ready to be your own boss,
that's the beauty of your smile.
Bring out the best in
it with Crest 3D White.
Crest removes 95% of surface
stains in just three days.
Crest, healthy, beautiful smiles for life.
- [Announcer] The 2020 race is revving up.
Live from Detroit, 20
candidates, two big nights.
The CNN Democratic presidential debates,
July 30th and 31st, only on CNN.
- Now that we're banking with Chime,
we get paid up to two days
earlier with direct deposit.
- And that makes my smile
up to two times bigger.
(lively music)
- [Announcer] Start banking
with Chime today at chime.com.
- Hey, I'm Zach, CEO of Roman.
Some health issues are
tough to talk about.
With Roman, you can go
online, chat with a physician,
and if treatment is right for you,
we'll ship FDA approved
medication right to your door.
Roman, let's take care of it.
(lively music)
- Hey, it's me, your fridge.
Aren't you forgetting something?
- Like what?
- Like changing your fridge filter, man.
- Woops.
- It's not that hard.
You don't even have to
remember which filter I need.
Just go to filtersfast.com.
FiltersFast.com has
this fast filter finder
that finds the right
filter for your fridge
and water quality for a
fraction of big box store prices
with their FiltersFast brand filters,
plus doorstep delivery and free shipping.
Do this for me, man.
Go to FiltersFast.com and
see how much you can save.
- [Announcer] CNN Special
Report, The Hidden Workforce,
Undocumented in America, Friday at 10.
(dramatic music)
- All right, that's it, let's roll.
Hey, let's be careful out there.
- [Female] Dispatch, we have a 911,
armed robbery in progress.
- [David] When quality
does emerge on television,
the phrase too good for TV is often heard.
One recent network offering that seems
to deserve that phrase
is Hill Street Blues.
(gun banging)
- Hill Street is one
of the changing points
of the entire industry
in the history of TV.
- We had all watched a
documentary about cops
and it had this real hand-held,
in the moment quality
that we were very enamored of.
(people shouting)
(telephone ringing)
- The minute you looked at
it, it looked different.
It had a mood to it.
You could almost smell the stale coffee.
- We didn't wanna do a
standard cop show where,
you know, you got a crime
and you got your two cops
and you go out and you catch the bad guy
and you sweat him and he
confesses and that's it.
Cops have personal lives that impact
their behavior in profound ways.
- Well, what about it?
Is he here or is he out there?
- Just don't get excited,
Counselor, we're working on it.
- How's this for logic, Furillo?
If he's not here and if he's
not elsewhere, he's lost.
- We didn't say that, Counselor.
- You've lost my client.
Never in my entire life have I listened
to so much incompetence covered up by
so much unmitigated crap.
Find my client, Furillo, or I swear,
I'll have you up on charges.
- There'd be these ongoing
arcs for these characters
that would play out
over five, six episodes,
sometimes an entire season and in a way,
for certain stories,
over the entire series.
And no on had really done that
in an hour long dramatic show.
- These past four months, I've missed you.
I had to find that out.
Come home, pizza man.
- I think in the past, people
had watched television passively.
And, the one thing I think we did set out
to be were provocateurs.
- The Eli Jackson report, you fill it out.
- What the hell's the
matter with you, man?
- I'll tell ya something,
they don't pay me enough
to deal with animals like this.
The first thing they see is a white face
and all they wanna do is dog ya.
- Listen to me, Renko, it was a white face
that pulled the trigger, not a black one.
It was a white one.
- It set a trend.
The idea that the audience
can accept its characters
being deeply flawed, even though
they were in this uniform.
I thought that that was
important to finally get across.
- Don't do that!
No biting!
- We wanted to make a show
that made you participate,
made you pay attention, and I
think that worked pretty well.
- And the winner is...
(laughing)
- Hill Street Blues!
(crowd cheering)
- We got 21 nominations and
we went on to win eight Emmys
and it put us on the map, literally,
and that's when people
finally checked us out.
- Programing chief of one of the networks,
he used to say to me about
shows like Hill Street
and St. Elsewhere, what
the American public wants
is a cheeseburger and what
you're tryin' to give 'em
is a French delicacy.
And he said, your job
is to keep shoving it
down their throat until after a while,
they'll say, that doesn't taste bad
and maybe they'll even order it themselves
when they go to the restaurant.
- Nice of you to join us, Dr. Morrison.
- The success of Hill Street
Blues as a critical phenomenon
influenced everything that came after.
And then, of course, you saw
shows like St. Elsewhere.
- Do you know what people cal this place?
Not St. Eligius, St. Elsewhere,
a place you wouldn't wanna
send your mother-in-law.
- When it first came on,
it was actually promoted
as Hill Street Hospital.
- You give your patients
the wrong antibiotics,
you don't know what
medications they're on,
you write the worst progress
notes, you're pathetic.
Pathetic!
- Phil!
- What?
- Dr. Morey needs you right away.
- I'm sorry.
- St. Elsewhere broke every rule there was
and then built some new rules.
- Bobby, the bloodbank
called a little while ago.
They ran a routine panel
on that pint of blood.
The T cell count was off.
- They would have tragic things
happen to these characters.
There was real heartache
in these people's lives
and you really felt for them.
- I've got AIDS?
- Television at its best is a mirror
of society in the moment.
- St. Elsewhere challenged
people and it challenged
you as an actor, much less
the audience, to think.
The stuff they gave you was
extreme and what they did,
whether they were dealing
with AIDS or having
one of their main doctor
characters raped in a prison,
they tackled lots of difficult subjects.
- St Elsewhere was run
by people who were trying
to stretch the medium and in the 80s,
television producers were
encouraged to stretch the medium.
- Okay, clear.
- As the 80s got serious,
there was more drama,
they were getting a little
bit more adventurous
with the types of shows
that were getting a shot.
- What are you doing?
- I'm doing what I--
- Should've done all along.
- What I wanted--
- To do originally.
- What I should've done--
- Last night.
Stop that, David!
- I'm calling--
- The police, David!
Hello, police.
- [Maria] The networks realized there was
an audience looking for
something less predictable
than traditional prime time fare.
- Moonlighting was another of those shows
that said, okay, I see the formulas
that we've had up to here.
Let's do different things.
(lively music)
- Hello.
We're looking a little
pale today, aren't we?
And who have we here?
- I don't know.
- Moonlighting was a
really experimental show.
They had a Shakespeare episode.
They had a black and white episode.
They did a musical episode.
They tried a lot of different stuff.
- I don't give a flying fig
about the lines in my face,
the crow's feet by my eyes,
or the altitude of my caboose.
- Well, I'm at a loss.
I don't know what a flying fig is.
- That's okay, they do.
(crowd cheering)
- There's no trouble on the set.
There is no trouble on set.
- Well, we have a very
volatile relationship.
There is a hate-love element to it.
(angrily mumbling)
- The flirtations were great,
Bruce and Cybil were great.
Glen Caron kept them apart for a long time
and bravo to him.
- What they did was they took
the Sam and Diane dynamic
from Cheers and escalated it.
Cheers was will they or won't they.
Moonlighting was do they even want to?
- Stay away from me.
- Here I come.
- But I don't want you.
I never wanted you.
- Yeah, right.
- Does entertaining mean, at some point,
stopping the tease of Dave and Maddie?
I mean, do they get together--
- I hope so.
- At some point.
- Well, that's gonna
be resolved this year.
We like to think of it as two
and 1/2 years of foreplay.
(hand slapping)
- People who've been watching
Moonlighting for years
were waiting for this moment.
(hand slapping)
And your emotions are already there,
built on to the emotions that
you're seeing on the screen.
So when Be My Baby by The
Ronettes starts playing,
it's like a perfect storm of romance.
(lively music)
♪ The night we met I
knew I needed you so ♪
(lively music)
- [Announcer] Here are even
more reasons to join T-Mobile.
One, do you like Stranger Things?
Sure you do.
That's why Netflix is on us.
Two, unlimited data.
Use as much as you want, when you want.
Three, no surprises on your bill.
Taxes and fees included.
Still think you have a better deal?
Bring in your discount and we'll match it.
That's right, T-Mobile
will match your discount.
(lively music)
- Let's be honest, you need insurance,
but it's not really
something you wanna buy.
It's not sexy.
- Ode to Esurance.
- Or delicious.
Or fun.
(lively music)
♪ Splash under the sun ♪
But since you need both
car and home insurance,
why not bundle them with
Esurance and save up to 10%,
which you can spend on
things you really wanna buy
like well, I don't know
what you'd wanna buy
because I'm just a guy on your TV.
Esurance, it's surprisingly painless.
(lively music)
♪ Take me to your best friend's house ♪
♪ Stroll around this roundabout ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
- What is that?
- Uh, mine, why?
- It's just that it's--
- Lavender, yes it is.
It's for men.
- But I like the smell of it.
(laughing)
(lively music)
- This is something big.
- This is something bigger.
(lively music)
- That is big.
♪ I'm moving on up-- ♪
- [Child Voiceover] Not as big as that.
- [Group Voiceover] Big!
- [Child Voiceover] Bigger!
Bigger!
- [Child Voiceover] This is big.
And that's bigger.
(lively music)
- [Ron Voiceover] Apollo 13 was
a real turning point for me.
- Houston, we have a problem.
- I learned the power of a true story,
how an audience begin to
lean in when they know
you're dealing with the truth.
(dramatic music)
- Coach, it's kind of
hard to see the ball.
- I've been there.
I had a TV service with
hardly any sports in 4K.
Couldn't see any of the quality details.
I switched to DirecTV.
Now I get the most live sports in 4K.
- So, how does that help me?
- It really doesn't.
I don't know why I told ya that.
Go get 'em sport.
- Live sports that aren't
in 4K are just kinda TV.
Don't just kinda TV, DirecTV.
Don't have 4K, call 1-855-Watch4K
and ask for it today.
- Mr. Goodson.
- Not enough shelter
for us people on the street.
- Who is us?
- [Female Voiceover] So now
is probably not a great time
to get my library card?
♪ We are ♪
- I am not prepared to be
in a standoff with a cop.
- [Stuart Voiceover] Why
do all this, for what?
- Let 'em know that we still matter.
(lively music)
- Sir, you're gonna have to
put your clothes back on.
- [Announcer] The
Public, buy or rent today
and watch any time, any where
on your favorite screens
with DirectTV Cinema.
Movies start at channel 125.
- [Announcer] New Day, tomorrow morning,
starting at six Eastern on CNN.
(dramatic music)
- There are a lot of people
who used to say, I was there.
Now people say they
watched it on television.
- There's just a lot
of excitement connected
to sports in the 80s.
You used to have to
depend on the five minutes
at the end of your local newcast.
There just hadn't been enough, you know.
Give us a whole network of sports.
- [Announcer] There's just
one place you need to go
for all the names and
games making sports news,
ESPN Sports Center.
- What happens in the 1980s
is sports becomes a TV show
and what are TV shows built around?
They're built around characters.
- You can't be serious, man?
You cannot be serious.
You guys are the absolutely pits
of the world, you know that.
- McEnroe, the perfect villain,
the New Yorker that people loved to hate,
or the cool Swede, never
giving any emotion away.
- What tennis really wants is
to get its two best players
playing over and over again in the final,
whether they're John
McEnroe and Bjorn Borg
or Chris Evert and Martin Navratilova,
that's what we wanna tune
into over and over and over.
(audience gasping)
- [Announcer] Oh goodness me, midcourt,
and three match points
to Martina Navratilova.
- Know that this man
has a smile that lights
up a television screen
from here to Bangor Maine.
- And then there's Magic Johnson,
this urban kid from
Michigan and Larry Bird,
this guy who worked carrying trash,
one plays for the Los Angeles Lakers,
the other plays for the Boston Celtics.
It's a great story.
- [Announcer] Lakers have several chances
and here's Larry Bird,
chugging down the court.
(audience cheering)
- [Announcer] Magic
Johnson leads the attack.
Look at that pass, oh ho,
what a show.
- What a great play!
- When those championship
games are in primetime
and people are paying attention to that,
television feeds into those rivalries
and makes them bigger than
they've ever been before.
- I dare them to challenge me
with their somewhat primitive skills.
THey're just as good as dead.
- Every Mike Tyson fight was an event
because every fight was like an ax murder.
When he fought Michael Spinks,
the electricity you could
just feel watching it on TV.
- [Announcer] Here comes Mike's hit,
he leads with the right
hand, there he goes!
- Tyson was made for TV
because there was drama.
- [Announcer] It's all over.
Mike Tyson has won it.
- [Roy] Not a lot of junior
high school kids can dunk,
especially at five feet.
- But everybody tries, man.
- (laughing) I bet, now.
- Everybody tries.
- I think that he is starting
to transcend just his sport,
that he's becoming something
of a public figure.
- Michael Jordan becomes the model
that every other athlete
wants to shoot for.
They wanna be a brand and that's
what television does for these athletes,
turns them into worldwide, iconic brands.
- [Announcer] The in bounce
pass comes in to Jordan.
Here's Michael on the foul line.
A shot on Ehlo, good!
The Bulls win it!
- Athletes, in the 80s, became
part of an ongoing group
of people that we cared about.
We just had an enormous,
pent-up demand for sports,
and the 80s began to
provide, thank goodness.
- Cable television is continuing to grow.
It's estimated that it will go
into one million more
US households this year.
- With cable television
suddenly offering an array
of different channel choices,
the audience bifurcated.
That's an earthquake.
- [All] I want my MTV.
- I want my MTV.
(lively rock music)
- A new concept is born,
the best of TV combined
with the best of radio.
This is it, welcome to
MTV, Music Television,
the world's first 24 hour
stereo video music channel.
- Music television, what a concept.
MTV was pow, in your face.
You were not gonna turn us off.
(lively music)
- MTV did nothing but play
current music videos all day long.
So let me get this strait.
You turn on the TV and
it's like the radio?
- I'm Martha Quinn.
The music will continue non-stop
on MTV Music Television,
the newest component
of your stereo system.
When MTV launched, a
generation was launched.
18 to 24 year olds were
saying, I want my MTV,
I want my MTV videos,
I want my MTV fashion.
- Yo.
- MTV was the first network really focused
on the youth market and
becomes hugely influential
because they understand each other,
the audience and the network.
- MTV had a giant impact,
visually and musically
on every part of the TV
culture that came next.
- Freeze!
- Freeze, Miami Vice!
(lively music)
- Friday nights on NBC
are different this season,
thanks to Miami Vice.
It's a show with an old theme,
but a lot of new twists.
Described by one critic as
containing flashes of brilliance,
nonetheless, shot entirely
on location in South Miami,
the story centers around
two undercover vice cops.
- I don't know how this
is gonna work, Tubbs.
I mean, you're not exactly up my alley,
style and persona wise.
Heaven knows I'm no box of candy.
- Television very much
was the small screen.
What was interesting about Tony
Yerkovich's pilot screenplay
for Miami Vice is that
it was exactly not that.
Very much the approach was, okay,
they call this a television series,
but we're gonna make one-hour
movies every single week.
- [Male Voiceover] Okay, here we go.
Stand by.
- And action.
- Police, police!
- [Jane] They were just
describing the show was sort
of a new wave cop show.
- Yeah, it's a cop show for the 80s.
We use a lot of MTV images and
rock music to help describe
the mood and feeling of our show.
(gun banging)
- In a lot of ways, you don't
get Miami Vice without MTV,
because in a lot of ways,
Miami Vice was a long video.
The music was such a
big part of that show.
- There was an allure to using great music
that everybody was listening to as opposed
to the routine kind of TV
scoring of that period.
(lively music)
♪ I can feel it coming
in the air tonight ♪
- Not only was it not afraid
to let long scenes play out,
it would drag; a car going
from point A to point B
could be a four-minute Phil Collins song.
And it was.
♪ Oh Lord ♪
- Being able to take a
television series like Miami Vice
and let's really kind of
rock and roll with this
until somebody says,
stop, are you guys crazy,
you can't do that, and nobody ever did.
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
- Freeze, police!
(gun banging)
- [Announcer] Former Special
Counsel, Robert Mueller,
testifies before Congress, live.
The Mueller Hearing, Wednesday, July 17th.
Coverage begins at 8:00 a.m. on CNN.
(dramatic music)
- [Announcer] The 2020 race is revving up,
live from Detroit, 20
candidates, two big nights.
The CNN Democratic presidential debates,
July 30th and 31st, only on CNN.
(dramatic music)
- Tell 'em we're flexible.
- Don't worry, my Dutch is okay.
- Just okay?
- Mm-hmm.
(speaking in foreign language)
- Tell him we need this merger.
- It's happening.
- [Announcer] Just okay is not okay,
especially when it comes to your network.
AT&T is America's best wireless network,
according to America's biggest test,
now with 5G evolution,
the first step to 5G.
More for your thing, that's our thing.
- Ah!
- Brain freeze!
- No, it's my teeth.
- [Announcer] New Crest
Gum and Sensitivity
starts treating sensitivity
immediately at the gum line
for relief within days
and wraps your teeth
in sensitivity protection.
- Oh!
- Your teeth?
- No, it's brain freeze!
(laughing)
- [Announcer] Crest.
- [Announcer] Summer's not the
time for making bucket lists.
Bookers know summer is for booking it.
(bell ringing)
Like booking a beach
side resort and ordering
two more tacos than you need to, check.
Showing the deep end who's boss, check.
Starting a scooter gang
with the fam, check.
- Awesome.
- [Announcer] Bookers know
summer won't last forever.
- You're gonna thank me.
- [Announcer] So be a
booker at Booking.com,
the word's number one choice
for booking accommodations.
(lively music)
- [Announcer] If you have
moderate to severe psoriasis
or psoriatic arthritis, little
things can be a big deal.
(lively music)
That's why there's Otezla.
Otezla is not an injection or a cream.
It's a pill that treats differently.
For psoriasis, 75%
clearer skin is achievable
with reduced redness, thickness,
and scaliness of plaques.
For psoriatic arthritis,
Otezla is proven to reduce joint swelling,
tenderness and pain.
And the Otezla prescribing information
has no requirement for
routine lab monitoring.
Don't use if you're allergic to Otezla.
It may cause severe diarrhea,
nausea, or vomiting.
Otezla is associated with an
increased risk of depression.
Tell your doctor if you
have a history of depression
or suicidal thoughts or
if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor your weight
and may stop treatment.
Upper respiratory tract
infection and headache may occur.
Tell your doctor about your medicines
and if you're pregnant or planning to be.
Ready to treat differently with a pill?
Otezla, show more of you.
- This is nice.
- Yeah, yeah, this is nice.
(chip crunching)
- Mm, how did you make the
dip so rich and creamy?
- Oh, it's Philadelphia--
- Family recipe.
- Can I see it?
- No.
- Philadelphia dips, so good,
you'll take all the credit.
(car beeping)
(tires squealing)
- [Announcer] Life doesn't
give you many second chances.
(dramatic music)
(car beeping)
(tires squealing)
But a Subaru can.
- You guys okay?
You all right?
- [Announcer] EyeSight
with Pre-Collision Braking,
standard on the Subaru Ascent.
Presenting the three-row Subaru Ascent.
Love is now bigger than ever.
- [Announcer] Closed captioning brought
to you by Mesobook.com.
- [Announcer] Mesothelioma is all we do.
For over 10 years,
we have offered a free
book on Mesothelioma.
Call 1-800-259-9374.
(dramatic music)
- In recent years, it
seems that television
has become a kind of
electronic confessional
where guests are willing to expose painful
and sometimes embarrassing
aspects of their lives,
quite readily, to millions of viewers.
- At the beginning of the decade,
we get the dominance of
Phil Donahue and that sort
of a maturation of women's
issues and he seemed
to talk to them in the audience,
he seemed to talk to them
through the TV screen.
- I'm glad you called; kiss the kids.
(audience laughing)
We'll be back in just a moment.
- If you look at the
body of work we've had,
you're gonna see the 80s there.
- I'm not here to say you're wrong,
but let's understand this.
When you bring a moral
judgment without knowing them,
against them, for the way that they look,
they feel that confirms the
reason for their rebellion,
if that's what you wanna call it.
(audience applauding)
- He really believed that
daytime television needed
to talk about the ideas
we were thinking about,
the issues we were concerned about.
- I don't wanna characterize his question,
but why don't you get this fixed instead
of doing this screwy stuff?
- There's not a single
recorded case in history
of any trans-sexual that ever,
through psychological treatment, changed.
It has never happened yet.
- And we were putting
very important people
on the program, all kinds of people,
gay people, people going to jail,
people running for office,
sometimes the same people.
It was a magic carpet ride.
You really do paint a
very, very grim picture
of the sitting president
of the United States.
- Let me just say this,
I think he's probably
the laziest president that I've ever seen.
- The audience for Phil
Donahue built and built
and built and built and
led the way to Oprah.
(lively music)
(audience cheering)
- Wooh!
Hello everybody!
Hello!
- Oprah has a particularly
magical combination
of her own background, her own experience,
her own incisive mind,
an empathetic spirit.
(audience cheering)
- Thank you,
I'm Oprah Winfrey and welcome to
the very first national
Oprah Winfrey show.
(audience cheering)
- I was surprised at the rocket
pace that Oprah took off,
because it took us a lot longer.
The Donahue Show rearranged the furniture,
but Oprah remodeled the whole house.
- There are a lot of
other people out there
who are watching who
really don't understand
what you mean when you
say, well, we're in love,
because I remember
questioning my gay friends,
saying, "You mean like,
you feel about him,
"the way I feel about--
(audience laughing)
- It's kind of a strange concept for a lot
of people to accept.
- Oprah was connecting
with people in a way
that no one had on TV before.
And it was really special to see.
- Did you know that for the longest time
I wanted to be a fourth
grade teacher because of you?
- I was not aware of inspiring anyone.
- I think you did exactly what
teachers are supposed to do.
They create a spark for learning
and that's the reason I
have a talk show today.
- Oprah Winfrey now dominates
the talk show circuit
both in the ratings and popularity.
- I want to use my life as a
source of lifting people up,
that's what I wanna do.
That's what I do every day on my show.
We get accused of being tabloid television
and sensational and so forth,
but what I really think we do,
more than anything else,
is we serve as a voice
to a lot of people who
felt up until, perhaps,
my show or some of the
others, they were alone.
This is what 67 pounds of fat looks like.
(audience chattering)
I can't lift it.
It is amazing to me that I can't lift it
but I used to carry it around every day.
- There's nothing more
endearing to an audience
than to have that kind
of honesty and humility
and courage on the part of a host.
And that, I think, has a
lot to do with her power.
- Feels like I can do some good here
and I really do think that
the show does a lot of good.
(lively music)
- American television is
drowning in talk shows,
but it's never seen anything
like Morton Downey, Jr.
- I wanna tell you this--
- Sit down and shut up!
- Other competitors come and
take the television talk show
into two different directions.
So you start seeing the phenomenon
of daytime television shows becoming
less tame and more wild.
- The 80s brought a lot of
belligerence to television,
whether it was Morton Downey, Jr.
being the offensive characturish person
that he was or Geraldo.
He did his own outlandish things.
- Stay with us, ladies and gentlemen.
We're gonna get into the mind
of another all-American boy
who came under the influence
of Satanism and took part
in a crime without passion or motive.
- Geraldo Rivera takes
the power of the talk show
to a whole other level,
trying to put people on stage
who hate each other, who are gonna fight.
- In the case of the temple of Satan
and the church of Satan,
we have not had any problems
with criminal behavior.
- Yet, when you hear story
after story after story
of people committing
these wretched crimes,
these violent crimes in the devil's name--
- The more tension there is,
the more conflict there is,
the more violence there is,
the more the ratings go up.
And the American people
love to complain about it,
but they also love to watch.
- Geraldo Rivera is back
in a controversy tonight.
Rivera drew sharp criticism with
his recent television
special on devil worship,
but today, he found himself
in a real free for all.
- I get sick and tired
of seeing Uncle Tom here,
trying to be a white man--
- Go ahead, Troy, go ahead.
- Now--
- Sit down, guy.
(audience chattering)
- Hey, hold it, hold it.
- Sit down, sit down.
(crowd screaming)
- [Tom] Rivera suffered a broken nose,
but he said the show
will be broadcast later
this month in its entirety.
- That's not something I would have done,
but there was a lot of hypocrisy.
And one of the major
magazines put the picture
of Geraldo getting hit
with a chair on the cover
and the article said, isn't this awful,
look what's happened to television.
And yet, they couldn't wait to use
it to sell their own magazine.
- Let's go to the audience, all right?
I want to stick to you guys, you guys--
- Over the years,
broadcasting has deteriorated
and now, in this era of deregulation,
it's deteriorating further.
- Give people light and they
will find their own way.
Relax; America will
survive the talk shows.
(lively music)
♪ Summer nights ♪
♪ Keeping me up ♪
♪ I wanna waste time ♪
♪ Just looking up the sky ♪
♪ Full of stars ♪
♪ Mind wandering far ♪
♪ Like I'm 16 dreamin' in the dark ♪
♪ Love the wind in my hair ♪
♪ As I drive my car ♪
- [Announcer] Right now,
lease the Infiniti QX50
for $379 a month plus get
a $1,000 summer bonus now
during the Infiniti + summer sales event.
(deep breathing)
- So I think we're going
with the family van.
- A family van?
Was that her choice?
- Nah, man, that was my choice.
This thing's got reclining
seats, DVD player,
it's got a built-in vacuum cleaner.
You ever seen my kid eat crackers?
- Yeah.
- See that, see how that works?
- Mm-hmm.
(vacuum whirring)
- Sometimes you just gotta
go straight for the source.
- [Announcer] Car loans fast
from Navy Federal credit Union.
Our members are the mission.
- Priceline will partner
with even more Vegas hotels
to turn their unsold
rooms into amazing deals.
Delegates, how do you vote?
(screaming)
(techno music)
That is freaky.
(applauding)
Priceline, every trip is a big deal.
(lively music)
- [Announcer] Discover new
San Pellegrino Essenza,
a twist of Mediterranean flavors
with the gentle bubbles of San Pellegrino.
Add a twist of flavor.
San Pellegrino Essenza,
tastefully Italian.
- Discover card.
- Hi, do you have a travel card?
- We do, the Discover It Miles card.
Earn unlimited 1.5
miles on every purchase,
plus we'll match your miles
at the end of your first year.
- You'll match my miles?
- Yeah, mile for mile, and no
black out dates or annual fee.
- Nice, I was thinking about
taking a scuba diving trip.
- I love that.
- Or maybe go surfing.
Or not.
- Okay, maybe somewhere else.
- Maybe a petting zoo.
- Can't go wrong.
- Can't get eaten.
- [Announcer] Earn miles,
we'll match 'em at the end
of your first year, plus no
annual fee or black outs.
The Discover It Miles card.
- I was so anxious to do
one line from the script,
"You complete me," there
were times that I thought,
is this too cheesy and I told Tom that.
And he said, "Just give me a shot at it."
- You complete me.
- I look around, everybody's crying.
Grissled guys holding
cable are like (sniffing),
I was like, I think it's
gonna work. (laughing)
- [Announcer] The movies
we love and the stories
behind them starts next on CNN.
- [Announcer] At touchofmodern.com,
all it takes is a touch
to create a world that's uniquely you.
(lively music)
Discover unexpected products
that turn the ordinary
into extraordinary, at touchofmodern.com.
- [Announcer] You wouldn't
do this to a room with a view
or hire a master chef
to cook for your dog,
or throw a pool party
with hardly any water.
So why would you watch a 4K
TV without 4K from DirecTV?
Lucky for you, DirecTV
delivers must-see originals,
hit movies on demand, and more live sports
and 4K than anyone else.
Stop missing out, call and ask
to activate 4K from DirecTV.
- [Narrator] No, wrong move.
Old fashioned bandages get dirty.
They can let in water and germs.
Look, it's falling off.
New Skin is the flexible liquid bandage
that seals out the bad stuff.
There's a spray, too.
- [Announcer] New Skin,
re-think how you heal.
- [Announcer] CNN Special
Report, The Hidden Workforce,
Undocumented In America, Friday at 10.
(dramatic music)
- [Kevin Voiceover] 1968, the summer
before junior high school,
and I don't mind saying
I was a pretty fair, little athlete.
- The Wonder Years was
a guy, in modern times,
looking back on his childhood.
That, in itself, is not new,
but The Wonder Years did it
with a wit and with the music.
It was a brilliantly written
show and a great performance
by that entire young cast.
- Hey, Steve.
It looks like my baby
brother and his girlfriend
have found each other.
- She's not my girlfriend.
- Kevin Arnold has to cope
with all the timeless problems
of growing up during one
of the most turbulent times
that we have known.
- Kevin Arnold is just like a regular kid,
except in the 1960s and
he's not really aware
of many of the events.
In one of the episodes,
the whole family's watching
the Apollo 8 take off,
but I'm just sitting there
trying to call a girl.
- The first episode of The Wonder Years,
anybody who saw it,
remembers the ending where,
you know, the first kiss
with Winnie and Kevin Arnold.
The song that they play is
"When A Man Loves A Woman."
That moment seemed so pure and so real.
♪ When a man loves a woman ♪
♪ Can't keep his mind on nothin' else ♪
- The tone of the baby
boomers of the 1960s
is about rebellion, about being students.
By the 1980s, it's time
to grow up, and so,
they shave their beards,
give up their dashikis,
and they put on power
suits, a whole new notion.
- Aw, the yuppies.
Last year, the politicians
were all talking
about winning their votes.
Now those young, urban
professionals and the rest
of their baby boom
generation are being wooed
by advertisers and their agencies.
- By the 80s, it was pretty
clear that the generation
after the generation of
the 60s may be embodied
by Alex Keaton on Family Ties,
seemed to be a lot more interested
in the corner office
than the new Jerusalem.
- You're a young man.
You shouldn't be worried about success.
You should be thinking about
hopping on a tramp steamer
and going around the world.
- The 60s are over, Dad.
(audience laughing)
- Thanks for the tip.
- You weren't laughing at
Michael J. Fox's character
for being too conservative.
You were actually laughing at the parents
for being too hopelessly liberal.
- What is this?
I found it in the shower.
- That's generic brand shampoo.
- Ah!
(audience laughing)
- This is him, this is the guy
I've been telling ya about.
This is everything you'd
want in a president.
- The genius of Family Ties is it allows
a kind of youthful Regeanite to emerge
that's focused more on the future,
that's focused more on
a critique of the 60s.
- Michael J. Fox as Alex
Keaton really became
the center of the show and
the writers were smart enough
to see that they had something special
and they wrote to that.
- It's not fair, Alex.
- Yeah, there's nothin'
you can do about it, Jen.
My advice to you is that you just enjoy
being a child for as long as you can.
I know I did.
It was the best two weeks of my life.
(audience laughing)
- Alex is a little Bill Buckley.
The Wall Street Journal is his Bible.
(laughing)
He has a tie to go with his pajamas.
He's very conservative and
very intense 17-year old.
(audience laughing)
The first thing your
teacher's gonna ask is what
you did over the summer.
Now, a lot of kids are gonna
say, I went to the zoo,
or I went to the beach, or
I went to a baseball game.
What are you gonna say?
- I watched the Iran Contra hearings.
(audience laughing)
- [Barry] If mom and dad
thought his generation
was going to the dogs, think again.
This is the generation that
has discovered hard work and success.
- American culture is changing in the 80s
and in terms of television,
there's a whole notion
of Demographic segmentation.
- Networks were beginning to not be afraid
to appeal to a very specific demographic.
- Hey handsome.
Look at that shirt.
Is that a power shirt, or what?
- Nice suit, Ellyn, good shoulder pads.
You look like you're
drafted by the Eagles.
- Ooh, hoo.
- Thirtysomethign said,
we're not gonna have cops,
lawyers or doctors.
We're just gonna be about people.
- What are we doing here?
Why did we start this business?
- To do our thing, but
right now, we got two wives,
three kids, four cars,
two mortgages, a payroll,
and that's life, pal.
You be the breadwinner now.
- Is that what I am?
- Thirtysomething is a very important show
as you're going into
this era of television
being more introspective
and more emotional
and some people weren't buying it.
But for other people,
when they were talking
about things like having
kids and who was gonna
go back to work and some of these issues
that hadn't been talked about a whole lot,
it was important to people.
(baby crying)
- I was so looking forward,
I was so looking forward to doing this,
to being a grown-up for just an hour.
- In the beginning, there
was talk of this being
the yuppie show and you
mentioned it tonight.
You said that if there were a category
for the most annoying show,
this might win as well.
- No, what some people
perceive as annoying,
it has nothing to do with yuppie.
I think yuppie is a word
made up by demographers
and advertisers to sell soap.
I don't think it has anything
to do with what the show is.
- Thirtysomething was not a giant hit,
but it was a niche hit.
It attracted an enormously
upscale group of advertisers.
- The network cared who was watching,
not how many were watching,
and that was more and more
catching on in the 80s.
(dramatic music)
- The prosecution will
ask you that you look
to the law and this you must do,
but I ask of you that you
look to your hearts as well.
Thank you.
- LA Law was partly a classic lawyer show.
But it was intertwined
with their personal lives
and different lawyers who
were sleeping together
and trying to get ahead.
- The reality level on
that show was like a foot
or two off the ground.
And you were willing to go with that
because it was a whole
new spin on a law show.
- Uh-uh, tell the truth.
If you had to do it all over again,
and she walked into your
office and she said,
"Take my case," would you?
- Well--
- Of course you would
because it is juicy,
newsy, exciting stuff.
- It was really fun to
take the Hill Street Blues
format and use it to frame
an entirely different social
and cultural strata with
vastly different results.
- I wonder if I might engage
with my client privately?
- Certainly.
- What are you doing for dinner tonight?
- I was planning on having you.
- Okay, skip lunch.
- The formula had gotten established
of how you can do a dramatic show and yet,
still have an awful lot of fun.
We didn't used to be able
to accept that very easily
in a TV hour and even
before the 80s are out,
it's like, oh, okay, I get it.
So it's like, all right,
what are the rules now?
- You say you're part of
a change that's going on.
Where is it coming from
and where's it going?
- I think it has to do with
networks being more willing
to put creative control
in the hands of producers,
who have strong view points
and letting them do what they wanna do.
- I think what Hill Street
Blues was and what Moonlighting
was is what the best television is,
is it distinguishes itself by its voice.
- What we're supposed to be here is
the one thing people can trust.
If you go out there like
a bunch of night riders,
what the hell are you but just
another vicious street gang?
- There was great writing in the 80s.
That was a core group of brilliant people.
- The audience's demands were changing.
- It's obvious television
has changed a lot
since the first Emmy was
awarded 35 years ago.
- It's as though the contemporary audience
was yearning for more
stories about themselves.
- Bye everybody out there on TV, bye.
- As the 80s came to an
end, everything changed.
- I think one of the, when
we look back at the 1980s,
10 and 20 years from now,
we're gonna be disgusted
at some of the TV that
you've just mentioned,
the super violent programs,
the terrible comedy shows,
but one of the great
things that's happening now
and will continue to happen increasingly,
throughout this decade,
is the replacement of rotten
entertainment programming
by news and talk and
information programming
on all three networks, very slowly.
- But will it be rotten news and uh--
- Well, I don't think, so far,
most of the news oriented programs,
magazines, information, talk shows,
and the networks, have been surprisingly,
at least to me, surprisingly good.
(dramatic music)