- Us a quote.
It was so easy.
Dan even helped pay to pack and move us.
MarketPro Homebuyers
truly helped my family
when we did not know what to do.
- [Narrator] Call us
today at 301-799-7355.
- [Narrator] From LeBron James.
- Victory's only a mile away.
- [Narrator] Million Dollar
Mile premieres this March.
(rock music)
(crowd cheers)
- Let's see, I've got
all my Super Bowl snacks.
I've got pigs in a blanket,
pigs out of blankets, and just blankets.
(audience laughs)
(doorbell rings)
Hey, it's my mutual Instagram
friend, Sir Patrick Stewart.
Hey thanks for being here.
I had no idea you were
such a Super Bowl fan.
- Oh, of course!
I love American football.
They get to use their hands.
(audience laughs)
Oh, let's get this mother started, yeehaw!
Yeah buddy!
Give me a beer!
(audience laughs)
(doorbell rings)
(audience cheers)
(ominous music)
- Gritty!
(audience laughs)
- Gritwold G. Grittington.
I hope you don't mind,
but I brought a friend.
He was just outside now, parking the van.
- Oh, sorry for the confusion earlier.
Shake?
(audience laughs)
- Gritty and I go way back.
We used to be in the Royal
Shakespeare Company together.
- Oh, sure, Hamlet.
- No, Gritty played Juliet.
I have no idea where the skull came from.
(audience laughs)
- Okiedoke.
♪ We'd better get a buzz going ♪
Who would like to shotgun a brewski?
(audience laughs)
(crowd cheers)
- [Announcer] Ball in the
air, and it's intercepted!
(whistle blows)
- One, two--
(doorbell rings)
Oh, doorbell.
(crowd cheers)
Speaker of the House, Nancy Pelosi
and Senate Democratic
Leader Chuck Schumer?
- Please Stephen, we're friends.
- Just call us Chuck and
Speaker of the House Nancy.
- Okay, so what are you guys doing here?
- We figured your little
get together needed us.
- Why is that?
- [Both] 'Cause we're the party leaders.
(rock music)
- Gritty!
(audience laughs)
Well I'm glad you're here.
Why don't you come on in?
- Oh no, there's more
trouble in Washington.
- We gotta go.
- Oh, okay.
- Juice it, Nancy!
- Thanks, thanks for stopping by.
(audience applauds)
Gritty, if that's out of tune.
(crowd cheers)
- Come on, get in there!
Knock his head off!
- Patrick, this is the halftime show.
♪ I got the moves ♪
- I'm aware of that.
Snap his femur!
(audience laughs)
(rock music)
- What do you wanna do now?
- Well, I hear there's
an all new Late Show.
- On Sunday?
- Mhmm.
- Let's check that out.
(crowd cheers)
Huh, that's weird.
Where's the host?
(crowd cheers)
Oh god!
I'm supposed to be there.
Captain, beam me up!
- Stephen, that's not a real thing.
(audience laughs)
- It is to me.
Gritwold.
(device beeping)
- Gritwold!
You have violated the prime directive.
Give that back to me.
- [Announcer] It's The Late
Show with Stephen Colbert
Super Bowl Edition.
Tonight, are you ready for some Late Show?
Plus, Stephen welcomes Conan O'Brien.
Musical guest James Taylor,
and a special appearance by Steve Carell,
featuring Jon Batiste and Stay Human.
And now, live on tape from
the Ed Sullivan Theater
in New York City, it's Stephen Colbert!
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheers)
- Woo!
Hello!
(crowd cheers)
Beautiful, please have a seat everybody.
Thanks so much.
Welcome one and all, ladies
and gentlemen to The Late Show.
I'm your host, Stephen Colbert.
Happy, happy Super Bowl Sunday.
(crowd cheers)
It's always an exciting night.
It's a great day, it's a great day.
It's a great day.
It's our one true national holiday.
This is the one day, when
despite our divisions,
Americans come together
around their TVs, and for
just one beautiful moment
don't fast forward
through the commercials.
(audience laughs)
- On this great Sunday.
- We all wanna see
which talking animal
wants to sell us beer.
(audience laughs)
Which celebrity really wanted the money.
I've been there, my brothers and sisters.
You enjoy that.
- On this great Sunday.
- Another annual tradition
is the pre-game presidential interview.
Goes back to the very first Super Bowl,
when Lyndon Johnson made
the surprise announcement
that he was sending both teams to Vietnam.
(audience laughs)
Yeah.
- Oh wow.
- Fun fact, that's how
the NFL draft started.
(audience laughs)
- Oh my!
- Last year, last, is this last year?
Last year, Trump skipped the interview,
but Friday he sat down
with Margaret Brennan
of CBS's Face the Nation,
and he brought the nation
a whole lot of face.
(audience laughs)
He started by describing how he believes
he's in a good position to
declare a national emergency
to get his border wall
when negotiations with
Congress end on February 15th.
- When you have people
dying all over the country
because of people like Nancy Pelosi,
who don't want to give
proper border security
for political reasons.
She's doing a terrible
disservice to our country,
and on the 15th we have now
set the table beautifully.
- Not a hopeful sign, 'cause
we all know what it looks like
when Trump sets the table beautifully.
(audience laughs)
And so, look how, look.
Look how beautiful.
Look how.
The subject turned to
sports when Brennan asked
if Trump would let a child
of his play football.
- It's very, it's a very tough question
and it's a very good question.
If he wanted to, yes.
Would I steer him that way?
No I wouldn't.
- Why?
- And he actually plays a lot of soccer.
He's liking soccer, and a
lot of people including me
thought soccer would probably
never make it in this country,
but it really is moving forward rapidly.
- Yes, we, we tried to keep
soccer out for a long time, but,
but it's hard, it's moving so rapidly.
That's how the caravan does it.
They just dribble their
kids up to the border,
and then just a little bit of that,
little bit of this, little bit of that.
Little dip dip, dah, dah, dah.
Little dah, and then they
bicycle kick him into El Paso.
(audience laughs)
Yelling goal!
That's really why we need the wall.
But it's so hard to build
when you can't use your hands.
(audience laughs)
Soccer, soccer.
(audience cheers)
Soccer Jon.
- Soccer.
Is that soccer, is it?
- And he explained his
concerns about football.
- I just don't like the reports that I see
coming out having to do with football.
- [Margaret] Concussions?
- Yeah, concussions and other things.
Knees and hips and shoulders
and elbows, and everything else.
- Heads, shoulders, knees, and toes.
Knees and toes.
(audience laughs)
Eyes and ears and mouth
and many people say,
and I'm hearing this a lot, and nose.
(audience laughs)
But, here's the deal.
Trump's not gonna be president forever.
(audience cheers)
Who knows?
- You get clapping for that.
- Who knows?
I don't know, I don't know.
- [Jon] They clapping for that.
- We're barely a month into 2019
and we've already got at
least 10 different candidates
hoping to secure the
Democratic Party's nomination,
'cause on Friday another
Democrat entered the race.
New Jersey senator and man trying to pass
universal healthcare with his mind,
(audience laughs)
Cory Booker.
Here's a little taste of Cory
Booker's video announcement.
- When I was a baby, my
parents tried to move us
into a neighborhood with
great public schools,
but realtors wouldn't sell us a home
because of the color of our skin.
So over 20 years ago, I moved into
the central ward of
Newark to fight slumlords,
and help families stay in their homes.
I still live there today.
- That is inspiring,
and I gotta say daring.
I've never seen anyone so
proud to be from Newark.
(audience laughs)
Newark, home of the airport
you didn't realize you were landing at.
(audience laughs)
Come, because you're lost.
Stay, because you're lost.
(audience laughs)
Remember when all those
parked cars caught on fire?
That was this week.
This week, in Newark.
(audience laughs)
And, there was a lot of not so subtle
anti-Trump messaging in this ad.
Booker tells the story
of a racist landlord
turning away his parents.
Imagery of kids in cages,
and of course a scene of him
in a barbershop, which is
an obvious dig at Trump
since it implies Booker could
grow hair, but chooses not to.
(audience laughs)
But, but.
(audience applauds)
♪ I don't believe it's fair ♪
- But Booker's taken a real risk
with the name of his campaign, Cory 2020.
Bold move, going with the first name.
If you'll recall, that did not work out
too well for Jeb! 2016.
(audience laughs)
Also, I don't know how I feel
about having a President Cory.
Sounds like a Disney show.
(audience laughs)
Probably because it was a Disney show.
(audience cheers)
We got a great show for you tonight.
Conan O'Brien is here!
But when we return, I become
a player in Madden NFL 19.
Stick around.
I'm passed the midway.
(audience cheers)
(pleasant music)
- [Announcer] The Late
Show with Stephen Colbert,
sponsored by Glad with Febreeze.
It neutralizes odors with the
irresistible scent of Gain.
- [Narrator] Nosy neighbor
with a keen sense of smell,
Glad bag full of trash.
What happens next?
Nothing.
Only Glad has Febreeze to neutralize odors
for five days, guaranteed.
Even the most perceptive
noses won't notice the trash.
Be happy, it's Glad.
(electronic dance music)
- [Narrator] With Advil liquid gels,
you'll ask what stiff joints?
What bad back?
Advil is relief that's
fast, strength that lasts.
You'll ask--
- What pain?
- [Narrator] With Advil liquid gels.
- I'll take a Coke.
- Is Pepsi okay?
Is Pepsi okay, wow!
Are puppies okay?
Is a shooting star okay?
Is the laughter of a small child okay?
Pepsi's more than okay!
It's--
(rings bell)
- Okay!
- Okurr!
♪ I like it like that ♪
♪ I said I like it like that ♪
- Okay, what have we learned today?
- You want a Pepsi?
- I want a Pepsi.
- There you go, okurr?
Ah, I've gotta come up
with my own catchphrase.
- Okay!
♪ Havana ooh nah nah ♪
♪ Half of my heart is ♪
(cupcake splats)
(Latin music)
(stomach gurgles)
♪ When you have nausea,
heartburn, indigestion ♪
♪ Upset stomach, diarrhea ♪
- Girl, Pepto ultra coating
will treat your stomach right.
♪ Nausea, heartburn, indigestion ♪
♪ Upset stomach, diarrhea ♪
- [Narrator] Try Pepto with ultra coating.
- [Narrator] Introducing
high-rise Rockstar 24/7 denim,
now with sculpt.
Hurry in to Old Navy for all
jeans on sale, up to 50% off,
with kids from $8, adults
from $15, only at Old Navy.
- [Narrator] With Expedia,
I saved when I added
a hotel to our flight.
So even when she grows up,
she'll never outgrow the
memory of our adventure.
Unlock savings when you add
select hotels to your existing
trip, only with Expedia.
- [Narrator] New Theraflu power pods,
the cold and flu fighting
machine you put in your machine.
Press the button to
brew a powerful relief,
to defeat your toughest
cold and flu symptoms fast.
New Theraflu power pods,
press, sip, relief.
- [Narrator] Wednesday.
- Ooh!
- [Narrator] The battle rounds
continue on the World's Best.
- Woohoo!
- [Narrator] The pressure's on,
as more fan favorites fight to stay alive.
♪ There's no way I will ♪
- [Narrator] Who will
survive the battle rounds?
- That's amazing!
- [Narrator] Find out on The World's Best,
Wednesday on CBS.
- [Narrator] If your
sister's teenage boyfriend
keeps hitting on you.
- See you later, ma'am.
- [Narrator] Can you catch him in the act?
- This is an insane idea.
- You got a better one, Mrs. Robinson?
(audience laughs)
- A new Fam, Thursday.
(pager beeps)
(upbeat music)
♪ Louie Louie oh no ♪
♪ See we gotta go ♪
- [Narrator] Bar Louie, join
the Gastrobar revolution.
What are you waiting for?
♪ Let's go ♪
(music chimes)
- [Narrator] Ready to conquer winter?
Then it has to be a Honda SUV.
More capable, with an
available turbo charged engine
and real-time all wheel drive.
More safety, with Honda Sensing,
including a collision mitigation system.
And less getting lost.
Get more this winter with a Honda SUV,
2019's best SUV brand.
Right now, get a 2019
CR-V for just 259 a month.
- Don't settle for less than a Honda.
- We didn't.
- [Narrator] See your
local Honda dealer today.
(upbeat music)
♪ Then again you're not yourself ♪
♪ Every day ♪
- Jon Batiste and Stay Human,
everybody, right over there!
Give it up for the band, there you go.
(audience cheers)
Well, Jon.
- Yeah?
- Boom.
- Yeah.
- Jon, I'm pretty excited.
We have our old friend, Conan O'Brien
coming out here in just
a minute, Conan O'Brien?
- Funny guy, he's a great guy.
Love Conan.
- James Taylor, James Taylor's
gonna perform here tonight
at the Ed Sullivan Theater, and we have
a special little game
we're going to be playing
with our good friend Steve Carell
is gonna be here tonight too.
- Oh yeah, y'all go way back!
- That's the best show.
This is the Super Bowl--
- Yeah you gotta do it.
- Tonight is the Super
Bowl of late night shows,
I gotta say, right now.
Also tomorrow, Taraji P.
Henson is gonna be here.
That's gonna be fantastic.
Never interviewed her
before, right first time?
Think so.
- Yeah.
- Of course, as I said this
is our Super Bowl special,
and I love football.
I've always wanted to play
the game professionally,
but my doctor says I can't
because I have a medical
condition known as mortality.
(audience laughs)
But there is some football
I am healthy enough to participate in,
the video game kind, and
luckily the good folks
over at EA Sports
agreed to make me a player
in the new Madden NFL 19.
(audience cheers)
- Yeah baby!
- Here's the deal.
I was excited, obviously,
but in order to make the most life-like
and accurate digital version of me,
they first needed hard data
on my athletic abilities.
(audience laughs)
So I headed out to the
Atlantic Health New York
Jets Training Center,
and put my skills to the test.
(intense music)
Stephen Colbert, Northwestern
University, theater major.
(intense music)
I've always been told I
don't have what it takes
to play professional football.
And that is true.
Luckily, the fine people at Madden NFL 19
agreed to put me in their game.
So I met with league player
ratings adjuster, Dustin Smith,
so he could rank my footbally-ness.
Dustin, can I call you Dusty?
- Uh.
- Dusty?
(audience laughs)
What's considered a good score?
What's the scale here?
- 99's the best.
- Okay.
What type of things are you gonna be
judging me in today, Dusty?
- Strength, speed, throw power,
kick power, kick accuracy,
catching, jumping.
- Is, there's no blood
test today is there?
Because I am high as a kite right now.
Anytime I know I need to use
my knees, I get an epidural.
(audience laughs)
What do you think my rating's gonna be?
- Conservative, 20.
(audience laughs)
- To help me figure
out just where I stand,
we brought in six foot four
New York Jets quarterback Sam Darnold.
Sam.
- Sir.
- Thanks so much for talking to me today.
- Absolutely.
- How old are you?
- I am 21 years old.
Yeah.
(audience laughs)
- And the fact that you are
younger than my oldest child is
in no way depressing to me.
- No, it's not a concern is it?
- Nope, no it's not.
But since you're on the Jets,
do you ever feel like breaking out
into singing songs from West Side Story?
- Um--
♪ When you're a Jet
you're a Jet all the way ♪
♪ From your first cigarette to your ♪
- Oh gosh.
♪ I like to live in America ♪
(audience laughs)
Come on!
- Come on you got it.
- You gotta.
- Where's Dusty?
Bring in Dusty.
- Do this Sam.
(dramatic music)
- I can't dance.
(audience laughs)
- [Stephen] It was time for my
first official test, catching.
- Ready, set hut!
Oh, you gotta jump up and grab it.
- What the hell is that?
What the hell is that?
(audience laughs)
- You gotta jump up and get the ball.
- How tall do you think I am?
- Set hut.
(audience laughs)
Are you serious?
- You throw that really hard.
- Set hut.
(audience cheers)
That was sweet.
- Okay.
- [Sam] That was really cool.
And the spin.
- [Stephen] Next up, throw under pressure.
- [Dustin] Throw under pressure.
- Throw under pressure, see that?
You could cut a diamond, all right?
Bring it.
- All right, guys.
(ominous music)
(audience laughs)
- Hi, Stephen.
Stephen, hi.
Nice to meet ya.
This is a comedy show.
Obviously you guys
were told that this is a comedy show?
(audience laughs)
Good, good.
Set hut!
(audience laughs)
- [Dustin] That's gotta
be like, the worst.
- 18, what the (bleep)?
I don't think Dustin's
giving me a fair shake.
I mean...
I'm a 54 year old man.
(audience laughs)
The doctor said I'd never be
able to comb my hair again.
(audience laughs)
It's like he doesn't even see
how I'm trying.
(audience laughs)
(emotional music)
Please don't use this.
(audience laughs)
Promise me.
Back on the field, 'cause
it's time for speed.
Just when you're ready to
go, just yell juice it!
- [Dustin] Juice it, you got it.
- I'm just trying to determine
which knee I want to pop first.
(audience laughs)
- Juice it!
(intense music)
(audience cheers)
(stopwatch beeps)
- Look at that.
- Woo!
Then my juke move.
I gonna juke ya, watch out!
Watch out, woo, woo!
Here we go, woo wah!
And finally, trucking.
- [Dustin] I'm gonna need you to
knock over one of these big fellas,
and you stay on your feet and keep going.
(audience laughs)
- Hut!
(dramatic music)
(audience laughs)
(Stephen grunting)
(audience applauds)
Time for my final rating.
What is my player rating,
and the important thing is
that I need to really know.
This is important, this is on television.
You have to tell me the truth,
and don't worry about my feelings.
I have a successful career,
I have a beautiful wife,
I have wonderful children.
Just be honest, it's important that I,
I know what the truth is,
and you're not gonna hurt my feelings.
- Okay, so officially, 19 overall.
(audience laughs)
- Stemming from my unfair rating,
I switched to an activity I excel at.
Sitting in a chair.
To create my digital player,
certified EA nerd Ben Haumiller
entered my test results.
Speed, strength, agility.
What has he got me for elusiveness?
- [Ben] 47.
- I could be way more elusive than that.
You wanna, I'll show you
how elusive I can be.
- Okay.
- Tell me you love me.
- I love you.
- God I don't deserve you.
(audience laughs)
See, you have no idea
whether I love you or not.
- I don't.
- Yet, I haven't said anything bad, okay?
That's elusive.
(audience laughs)
Okay let's take a look at me, here we go!
Okay that looks like me.
Let's do-ee.
Oh good, I'm wearing glasses.
So few football players do.
Is there any way to take this uniform off?
'Cause I've never seen me
with anything approaching a male physique.
- We are an E for everyone game.
- Okay.
- So.
Actually would you like to run a play?
- Sure.
There I am, as a quarterback,
and I already have a penalty.
What the hell just happened?
What did I do?
- [Ben] You're not happy
as the coach, either.
- [Stephen] Yep, how old
do you, wait a second.
How old did you make me as the coach?
- [Ben] Oh come on, you're
smoothed out right there.
You're looking all right.
- [Stephen] You look
like you carved my head
out of an apple core and
let it dry in the sun.
Good god, man.
- [Man] Here we go now!
- All right, in the pocket, bullet!
And, I suck.
I suck in real life.
Why would I want to suck in a game?
Look, even I'm mad at me.
I agree with that guy.
Now Ben.
- Yes?
- This is all just zeroes and ones, right?
- [Ben] Mhmm.
- Well what if I gave you a one
with two zeroes behind it,
would that help change my profile?
- I like this.
- Thank you.
With that and just a few clicks,
Ben pumped up all of my stats
and gave me a tight end.
Oh yeah.
(audience laughs)
Badonk-a-donk.
Back it up like a Tonka truck.
God I'm magnificent.
And, go.
(dramatic music)
Here we go, drills it!
Here comes the pain train!
All aboard, unh!
- Touchdown!
- [Stephen] Woo!
How do you like me now?
Boom.
- Right there.
- Woo, woo!
Oh come on, woo!
(audience cheers)
Thank you EA Sports,
thank you New York Jets!
We'll be right back with Conan O'Brien.
(audience cheers)
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] When you find
yourself in a strange land,
discover your inner hero,
and unlock the power
to speed through everything.
(engine revs)
In the blink of an eye.
Hertz Fast Lane, powered by Clear.
In select airports, 2019.
Hertz, we're here to get you there.
Marvel Studios Captain Marvel
in theaters March eighth.
♪ It's the soft ♪
- Charmin Ultra Soft?
- It's softer than ever.
- [Narrator] Charmin Ultra
Soft is softer than ever,
so it's harder to resist.
(record scratches)
- Okay, this is getting a little weird.
- [Narrator] Enjoy the go, with Charmin.
- [Narrator] When you brew
beer for over 250 years,
you become surrounded by ritual,
but there is none so powerful
as a simple toast to your health.
Or as we say in Ireland, slainte.
- [Narrator] For mild to moderate eczema,
there's Eucrisa.
It's steroid-free.
Do not use if you are allergic to Eucrisa
or its ingredients.
Allergic reactions may occur
at or near the application site.
The most common side effect
is application site pain.
Ask your doctor about Eucrisa.
(dramatic music)
(dinosaur roars)
(alarm blares)
(King Kong roars)
(train whistle blows)
- [Narrator] Wake up where the action is.
Stay at a Universal Hotel
with three epic theme
parks outside your door,
and now save up to $150
when you book by March 14.
- Their bearnaise sauce
here is the best in town.
Uh, what do you do for fun?
- Not this.
- Hm, oh.
What am I into?
Mostly Progressive's Name Your Price tool.
Helps people find coverage
options based on their budget.
Flo has it, I want it, it's a whole thing,
and she's right there.
- Yeah, she's my ride.
This date's lame.
He has pics of you in his phone.
- [Man] They're very tasteful.
- Julie means more to me than anything,
and I wanted to ask you, before I ask her,
may I have your permission to marry her?
- [Narrator] You're marrying
her, and her whole world.
Shop Neil Lane diamond
engagement rings at Kay.
(gentle piano music)
- [Narrator] This March, the chase is on
in the streets of LA.
♪ My feet go boom boom boom ♪
- To win one million, just run one mile,
through one punishing course.
There's only one catch, don't get caught.
- [Narrator] From executive
producer, LeBron James,
and host Tim Tebow.
- With an elite athlete on your heels,
you gotta be quick on your feet.
♪ Boom boom boom ♪
- [Narrator] Million Dollar Mile
premieres CBS Wednesday March 27.
♪ Boom boom boom ♪
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] In DC, great weather days
are powered by Sheehy.
- [Narrator] What is Verify?
- I keep seeing stories about felons
that are running for Congress.
Could you verify?
- [Narrator] You ask the questions,
Verify will do the digging.
- Nicole, yeah, we can
verify that for you.
- [Narrator] Verify, look into it.
- We need paperclips.
- I will go get some.
- Hi, excuse me, you can't just
go and take people's things.
- Okay.
- Mother of the year.
- Cool.
- If you haven't figured it out by now,
life becomes very complicated.
♪ But don't I make it look easy ♪
♪ Don't I make it look good ♪
- Oh my god, I am not reading
your texts with your wife.
I hope she orders the prawns.
♪ Hey ♪
- [Narrator] Better Things.
For more information,
go to FXNetworks.com.
(upbeat music)
(audience cheers)
- Welcome back everybody!
Ladies and gentlemen,
my first guest tonight has
written for The Simpsons and SNL,
and after 25 years he's
the elder statesman
of late night hosts.
Please welcome back to the show,
my friend and yours, Conan O'Brien.
(audience cheers)
(upbeat music)
- Thank you very much!
- Conan O'Brien.
(audience cheers)
Nice to see ya.
- Thank you very much,
it's a lovely crowd.
- They're lovely, they're lovely people.
- Thank you.
- It's very exciting to see Conan O'Brien.
- What a day--
- Back on the East Coast.
- What a day.
- It's always a treat for us.
- Yep, back in town.
- Yeah.
- Big day.
- For the Super Bowl.
- The Super Bowl.
- The Super Bowl obviously.
- That was a crazy game.
- It was.
(audience laughs)
You have exciting news.
The new Conan.
- It's really not.
It's the same Conan.
It's the same Conan--
- You're the same Conan,
but it's a new format.
- It's a new format.
- New set.
- Doing it for so long, I said
that let's do half an hour
because we noticed that our
crowd after a half an hour,
they were like, we're good.
(audience laughs)
- Really?
- Anyway.
- I think in show business we call that
leave 'em wanting some.
- Yeah.
(audience laughs)
No even at half an hour they're like,
you know you could go to 15, so.
(audience laughs)
- Now, there's tonight obviously
you're dressed beautifully,
but suede, a suede jacket.
- Yeah.
- I'm seeing a lot more leather jackets.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Denim, a lot more denim for you.
No more suits.
- Yes, I like to look like a
prosperous farmer, you know?
(audience laughs)
A farmer who's invested well in high tech.
That's the look I'm going for.
Yeah, no it's important to me.
I got tired of wearing the suit,
and I think the suit's great,
but I did it for so many years I thought--
- You said that like you were afraid
to hurt the suit's feelings.
(audience laughs)
Suit's great, suit's fantastic.
- I'm sorry, suit,
there's a suit right here
going come on, give me a chance.
(audience laughs)
No, it looks great, it looks terrific,
but I feel like you're
interviewing me for a bank loan.
(audience laughs)
I wanted to just sort of,
(chuckles)
I'm a real hard worker.
(audience laughs)
I wanted to kind of just
wear the kind of clothes
that I do in real life.
The only thing that's important to me
is that I wear a jacket.
I have to wear a jacket.
- Why is this?
- Thank you for asking.
(audience laughs)
It's going just as we rehearsed.
I wear, I have to wear a jacket
'cause I have to break up
where the middle of my body is
because I have a, and
this is a confession.
I have a very disproportionate body.
When I was 14 years old,
I had a massive growth spurt, massive.
I am six feet four.
I became, I went from being a kid
to six feet four overnight,
literally overnight.
What happened is my legs
grew and grew and grew,
and my torso never did.
(audience laughs)
I have the legs, the legs of an NBA center
and I have the torso of a little girl.
(audience laughs)
And you know what?
She's not even a healthy little girl.
She was born in the
1840s, her name's Molly,
and she has rickets.
(audience laughs)
- We actually have, we have
an image of your torso.
- Oh that's great, thank you very much.
That's my torso right there.
That was from a long
time ago, yeah thanks.
- Right there.
- Thanks for showing that!
- You look fine.
- Thank you.
- That's funny.
No one mentioned you'd
be showing that photo.
(audience laughs)
- Keep up the B-12.
- Yeah.
But it is, I have and so
I have very very long legs
and then this tiny little torso
that sits atop the, and
people think I'm exaggerating,
but I can prove to you that I am not, no.
(audience cheers)
Look at this.
This.
(audience cheers)
This is my natural.
And look, Stephen.
- Yes?
- I look like a shorebird
avoiding an oil spill, don't I?
(audience laughs)
It's just a freak show,
and then I have this
little R2-D2 body on top.
(audience laughs)
(beeping noises)
It's a freak show, it's a freak show
and it's caused me--
(audience cheers)
- It is.
- And I have--
- No photographs, no papier-mache.
He is alive.
- He's alive, he's alive!
(audience laughs)
And my pants, I'm always
pushing them down.
They're pushed down now.
They are artificially pushed down.
My penis is here.
(audience laughs)
When I use a urinal, I
have to flip the tie back.
(audience laughs)
Unbutton two buttons, ladies, not one.
Lean down, take care of business.
- Sure, sure, sure.
- It's a bad scene, man.
A real bad scene.
- So no more suits, so no more suits.
- You break it up a little bit.
I realized I just undid all
the good I'm trying to do
by displaying my body, but yeah.
It's been a source of great shame for me,
and I want other kids out there--
- I'm glad, I'm glad, I'm glad.
- You're glad that I feel shame?
- Yes, a little shame is a good thing.
- It's a very good thing.
- After, 25 years on the air.
The show has changed.
What else have you learned
about yourself over the years?
Because certainly you, when
you do one of these shows
you learn what you're capable of,
but then you find out things
about yourself that you never knew.
- Yes, I found out, and this
isn't even through the show.
This is just life as you go on in life,
when I started my show
I had just turned 30.
I didn't know who I was yet.
I've grown up and become sort of a man.
(audience laughs)
On television over this last 25 years,
but I'm finding out new
things all the time.
I found out, I went to go see my doctor
a couple of months ago,
and just for a physical.
He was doing the physical, and he said
"By the way Conan, I don't
know if you're into this,
"but I do DNA testing,
I'm very good at it.
"We could find out about your heritage."
I think some people
have done that 23andMe.
I said, sure, let's do it.
So he took a DNA sample,
and I left.
Two weeks later, he called me up
and he said, "I've never, ever, ever,
"had a DNA result like this before,
"and I've been doing this for 10 years."
And I said what is it?
And he said you are, this is true,
"You are 100% Irish."
(audience laughs)
Now listen, there's more, hold it.
He said you are 100%.
He said, "I've never
seen a 100% anything."
He said I've been doing this a lot.
I've done it with lots of people.
I've seen 93.5, I've seen 96.1,
I've seen 96, there's no
such, no one is 100% Irish.
He said if you go to Ireland,
and I looked it up and it's true,
and you get their DNA samples,
you will find out that the
most Irish looking people
are like 86% Irish, 94% Irish.
The Lucky Charms leprechaun,
true fact, 11% Spanish.
(audience laughs)
I, he said you're 100% and I said,
I didn't know what to make of this.
I said, what does it mean?
He said, what does it mean?
It means you're inbred.
(audience laughs)
And he said it, he said it just like that!
He said it like that, you're inbred
and I was like, what?
I mean, first of all that's very rude,
but then all this stuff
started to make sense
to me, you know what I mean?
(audience laughs)
Suddenly, everything came together.
(audience cheers)
- Well can I ask,
if you don't mind me asking,
in your generation is your wife Irish?
Did you--
- Well here's where it gets crazy, okay?
Because I, you know I looked into it
and I found out that the
reason I'm 100% Irish
is that my people, we came to Boston
around the time of the Civil War.
We just all moved into a very small area,
a corner of Worcester, Massachusetts,
and we just--
- Woo!
- Don't woo Worcester.
No one woos Worcester.
(audience laughs)
It's un-wooable, anyway.
They moved into a small corner
of Worcester, Massachusetts,
all lived in one house and
married each other for 180 years.
That's what they did,
and I realized, and then
I saw that my brothers
were marrying 100% Irish women,
and having kids that look like those kids
that would be like ah we're
off to get on the Titanic.
It'll all go well, you know?
So Irish-looking, and so I,
I, I stopped the madness.
I stopped the madness.
Let me tell you about my wife.
Been married 17 years,
I love her to death.
My wife is 50% Irish.
(audience laughs)
25% Scottish,
25% Welsh, and I swear
to God in my family,
they act like Conan got jungle fever.
(audience laughs)
(audience applauds)
(Stephen coughs)
(Conan chuckles)
My brothers are like, what's it like man?
You went crazy!
(audience laughs)
- Conan airs weeknights on TBS,
and new episodes of the podcast
Conan O'Brien Needs a Friend
are available every Monday.
Conan O'Brien everybody.
When we come back,
I share some personal
space with Steve Carell.
Thank you Conan!
- [Narrator] Whether
you bath in the bathtub,
or bath in the sink,
softer water's the water
your skin wants to drink!
With hard water, skin can dry out more.
Culligan water is what
your skin's crying out for,
'cause skin is important
whether you're a baby or bald.
That's why we say get a Culligan
water softener installed.
(soothing music)
- [Narrator] Every
material purposely chosen,
every texture thought out,
every button debated,
until the all wheel drive lock kicks in.
Then it's kinda anything goes.
(engine revving)
(soothing music)
(thunder booms)
(rain patters)
- [Narrator] If your day doesn't unfold
as predicted, unfold this.
New Neutrogena makeup remover single,
and remove 99% of makeup,
100% rain or shine.
Neutrogena.
- I'm missing out on our family outings
'cause I can't find a bladder
leakage product that fits.
Everything was too loose.
But Depend Fit Flex feels tailored to me.
- [Narrator] With a range
of sizes for all body types,
Depend Fit Flex underwear is
guaranteed to be your best fit.
- Mhmm.
- Mm, mhmm.
- Mm mm-mm.
- Mm?
- Mhmm.
- [Narrator] TGI Friday's big ribs.
Bigger, bolder, meatier.
Just 12.99 for a full rack and two sides.
TGI Friday's, where every
night the apps are endless.
- [Narrator] Higher higher.
- [Man] You won't last a week.
- [Narrator] Further.
- [Man] They'll never let you fly.
- [Narrator] Faster.
- [Man] Give it up!
- I'm done with you
telling me what I can't do.
(intense music)
- [Narrator] Captain Marvel, rated PG-13.
- Last weekend in Miami was great,
though I thought the
place was a bit expensive.
- I actually thought I got a
pretty good deal on a hotel.
- Seriously, you thought
$200 was a good deal?
- No, I'd never pay that for a hotel.
- Trivago.
- Well how'd you do it then?
- Yes!
How?
With Trivago, you can search
for the hotel you want,
select the dates, and Trivago
will compare the prices
for that hotel from hundreds
of websites worldwide
to find the ideal hotel for you.
- You look familiar, do I know you?
- Hotel?
- Trivago.
(upbeat music)
- Why shop Marshalls?
Because.
- Their prices will thrill you.
- [Girl] Woohoo!
- The brands will surprise you, muah.
- And every trip feels
like an instant victory.
- [Narrator] Marshalls, never
boring, always surprising.
- I can't believe it.
- That there's a lobster in our hot tub?
- [Lobster] Oh, you guys.
There's a jet!
Oh, I needed this.
- No, I can't believe how easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
our car insurance with Geico.
We could've been doing
this a long time ago.
- [Lobster] So you guys
staying at the hotel?
- Yeah, we just got married.
- [Lobster] Oh congratulations.
- Thank you.
- [Lobster] Yeah, I'm
afraid of commitment.
You know?
And being boiled alive, oh shoot.
- [Narrator] Believe
it, Geico could save you
15% or more on car insurance.
- [Lobster] Ooh, that guy's the worst.
- Tonight Chelsea Peretti,
Neil Patrick Harris,
standup from Adam Niemann,
plus Neil crashes my Q&A.
- This is another question for Neil.
- There's no way we could do it,
'cause Neil Patrick Harris isn't--
(audience cheers)
- [Narrator] Survivor Wednesday.
One castaway is pushed to her limits.
- I'm stranded!
- [Narrator] Four returning players
have a target on their backs.
- I want to blend in with everybody else.
- She might have to go.
- [Narrator] And nothing can prepare you
for how this one ends.
- Oh my god.
- [Narrator] New Survivor,
Edge of Extinction,
CBS Wednesday.
- [Narrator] We give Kias
advanced safety features.
We give them enduring quality.
We give it everything.
And this President's
Day, get 4,000 total cash
on the purchase of a 2019 Sorento V6.
Head to your local Kia dealer today.
- [Narrator] You.
All of you.
How you live,
what you love.
That's what inspired us
to create America's
most advanced internet.
Internet that puts you in charge.
- [Man] You boys have to eat.
- [Narrator] That
protects what's important.
That handles everything,
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond Wi-Fi.
This is xFi.
Simple, easy, awesome, Xfinity.
The future of awesome.
- [Narrator] We give Kias
advanced safety features.
We give them enduring quality.
We give it everything.
And this President's
Day, get 4,000 total cash
on the purchase of a 2019 Sorento V6.
Head to your local Kia dealer today.
(upbeat music)
- Hey everybody, welcome back!
Now Steve, obviously
we've known each other
a long, long time.
- Yeah.
- But you're a very private person.
You know?
- So are you.
- Yeah.
But, doing these interviews
sometimes can feel false,
or kind of forced in front of an audience,
because I know you're being honest
and you're telling me how you really feel,
but there's an audience here watching us.
- Right, you have to
monitor yourself I think.
- And also there's a little
bit of a performance energy.
- For sure.
- Putting on a face
for the faces that you meet.
I'd love to take a moment
just to talk to you
in a more personal, like a close way,
like in a private space.
- I would really love that.
(audience laughs)
- Well I'm so glad to hear that.
Join us now in The Late
Show's Personal Space.
(dramatic music)
(audience cheers)
Steve.
Long time viewers will know
this is The Late Show's Personal Space.
Steve Carell, I'll see you in the box.
(audience laughs)
(audience applauds)
We've known each other
for 30 years, right?
1988.
- It's been a long time.
- Yeah.
Honestly Steve, what was
your first impression of me?
- Well, if I'm completely honest,
you were very handsome.
(audience laughs)
You were talented, intelligent,
and there was a certain joie de vivre
that felt like it,
it was just different than
the other guys at Second City.
- Oh well thanks so much, man.
- What was your first impression of me?
- He is going to be so
handsome in his late fifties.
(audience laughs)
I mean really, that guy's gonna blossom.
- That's so--
- Why did you wait so long to get sexy?
(audience laughs)
- You know what?
I just, I just figured it was about time.
(audience laughs)
- You are aware that now you are a hot
salt and pepper zaddy, right?
(audience laughs)
You have to have heard this, right?
(audience cheers)
Can't get out of the box.
Can't, you're stuck in the box.
- You're embarrassing me!
(Stephen chuckles)
- Are you ever sick of people
quoting The Office to you?
- No, I love it.
- That's what she said.
(audience laughs)
(audience applauds)
- Can I admit something to you?
- Oh you can, it's Personal Space, Steve.
- The components of both of our breath,
(audience laughs)
is really warm.
- It is, it is getting
a little steamy in here.
Would you like, you used to be,
you're famously a bit of a sweater.
- Yeah.
Would you?
- It's happening.
(audience laughs)
- It is, it is, would you like a fan?
- Sure, do you have a fan?
(audience laughs)
- How's that feel?
- That's--
- Is that good?
- That's actually a lot better.
- That is really dangerously
close to my right eyeball.
(audience laughs)
- Is that a rubber tipped fan?
- Let's find out.
- Let me check.
(audience laughs)
Ah.
- Yes, yes.
Would you, would you like a mint?
- I would like a mint.
Oh!
(audience laughs)
(audience cheers)
I have a feel,
I have a feeling that this
is going to be a meme.
(audience laughs)
Maybe we shouldn't do that anymore.
- Okay.
(audience laughs)
- It really is, it's
really good to see you.
- It really is good to see you too.
Can I ask you a question,
and I want you to be honest.
- Sure.
- I mean it when I was joking before,
but you really, you look fantastic.
You have just aged like just
a fragrant cheese, and--
- Thank you.
- You look fantastic.
Do I,
do I look old to you?
- Do you look old?
No, you look fantastic too.
- Steve.
- You look exactly--
- Steve, Steve,
you're not gonna hurt my feelings.
Just be honest.
It's important to me.
You're not gonna hurt my feelings.
- Okay, I'll be honest.
You do look great.
(audience laughs)
(audience cheers)
- Why did you switch to drama?
You are one of the funniest people I know.
You can make anything funny.
Why did you, is it,
why did you become a dramatic actor?
- All I want is to be respected,
and to be pretentious.
(audience laughs)
- You're halfway there.
(audience cheers)
Steve Carell everybody!
We'll be right back!
(upbeat music)
(audience cheers)
- I wanted more from my COPD medicine.
That's why I've got the power of
one, two, three medicines with Trelegy.
The only FDA approved
three-in-one COPD treatment.
♪ Trelegy ♪
♪ The power of one two three ♪
♪ One two three ♪
♪ Trelegy ♪
- With Trelegy and the
power of one, two, three
I'm breathing better.
Trelegy works three ways.
To open airways, keep them open,
and reduce inflammation for
24 hours for better breathing.
- [Narrator] Trelegy won't
replace a rescue inhaler
for sudden breathing problems.
Trelegy is not for asthma.
Tell your doctor if you
have a heart condition,
or high blood pressure before taking it.
Do not take Trelegy more than prescribed.
Trelegy may increase your risk of
thrush, pneumonia, and osteoporosis.
Call your doctor if worsened breathing,
chest pain, mouth or tongue swelling,
problems urinating, vision
changes, or eye pain occur.
- Think your COPD
medicine is doing enough?
Maybe you should think again.
Ask your doctor about once daily Trelegy,
and the power of one, two, three.
♪ Trelegy one two three ♪
- [Narrator] Save at trelegy.com.
- [Narrator] My digestive system
used to make me feel sluggish,
but now I take Metamucil every day.
It traps and removes the
waste that weighs me down,
so I feel lighter.
Try Metamucil, and begin to
feel what lighter feels like.
♪ Havana ooh nah nah ♪
♪ Half of my heart is-- ♪
(cupcake splats)
(bell dings)
(Latin music)
(electronic dance music)
- I work hard to protect this Tookus.
To take care of any messy situations.
And put irritation in its place.
(keys jingle)
And if I can get comfortable
keeping this Tookus safe and protected,
you can get comfortable
doing the same with yours.
Preparation H, get comfortable with it.
(intense music)
- [Narrator] You gotta
be quick on your feet
when an elite athlete's on your heels.
Million Dollar Mile, CBS this March.
- We're lawyers.
We don't pursue ideals,
we pursue outcomes.
(intense music)
- Go pack, we're headed to a war zone.
- We will punish the
Marines who did this to you.
- Marines first, lawyers second.
That still the thinking back at Quantico?
- Of course.
- [Narrator] The Code, series
premiere April 19 after NCIS.
- You know what you taught me, Granny?
- How to accessorize.
- Yeah.
- How to cheat at poker.
- Well no, but--
- French cuss words?
- Yes, but also how to make
real southern butterfly shrimp.
- You gotta use buttery
crackers for the crust,
and fry 'em up fresh.
- Yes ma'am!
- Mm, this lemon mustard is fantastic!
- You taught me everything I know.
- Like roller derby.
- [Narrator] Eight cracker crusted shrimp,
plus a side of biscuit and lemon mustard
for just five bucks.
Thanks, Granny.
- [Narrator] They say
it's time to pack it in.
When the snow piles
up, and the air chills,
put your feet up and wait it out.
We have different plans.
(intense music)
♪ I was waiting for this ♪
♪ Mind over matter ♪
- [Narrator] Finance and get
$4,000 combined cash allowance,
plus $500 President's Day bonus
cash on the 2019 Cherokee.
(upbeat music)
(audience cheers)
- [Narrator] Colon cancer screening
for people 50 and older at average risk.
- I think it's time for a new screen.
For a different kind of
screen for colon cancer.
Thought about it?
His wife asked about screening options,
and her doctor ordered me.
I'm Cologuard, the noninvasive
test you use at home.
No special drink, just
a trip to the bathroom.
- [Narrator] Cologuard,
colon cancer screening
that's as easy as get, go, gone.
Cologuard is not right for everyone,
so ask your doctor if it's right for you.
(dramatic music)
♪ It's taking over ♪
♪ There's no escape ♪
♪ You better get movin' ♪
♪ Ready or not ♪
♪ It's about to go down ♪
♪ Here it comes now ♪
♪ Get ready ♪
♪ Oh oh get ready ♪
♪ Movin' ready or not ♪
- [Narrator] New Galaxy, free
buds, music to your ears.
Get free Galaxy buds when you
pre-order Galaxy S10 or S10+.
- [Narrator] Great news,
Liberty Mutual customize--
- I deliver the news around here.
Sources say Liberty Mutual
customizes your car insurance
so you only pay for what you need.
Over to you, logo.
♪ Liberty liberty liberty liberty ♪
- You'd rather dog sit
Cupcake than clean the toilet?
(rain pattering)
Oh come on!
With Scrubbing Bubbles,
cleaning doesn't have to stink.
The foaming bubbles make
your toilet super fresh!
It's cleaning reinvented.
- [Narrator] S.C. Johnson.
(people chattering)
- [Narrator] Introducing high-rise
Rockstar 24/7 denim, now with sculpt.
Hurry in to Old Navy for all
jeans on sale up to 50% off,
with kids from $8, adults
from $15, only at Old Navy.
- [Narrator] When you brew
beer for over 250 years,
it becomes surrounded by ritual.
But there is none so powerful
as a simple toast to your health.
Or as we say in Ireland, slainte.
- [Narrator] The Hyundai
President's Day Sales Event
is going on now.
Get huge savings on our full
lineup of cars, and SUVs.
Hyundai is also making
some history of its own.
The Hyundai Kona has been named
the 2019 North American
Utility Vehicle of the Year.
Incredible vehicles, monumental savings.
Find yours during the
Hyundai President's Day
Sales Event going on now.
Get an Elantra starting at 15,400,
or get up to 2,300 cash back,
now extended an extra $500
for government employees
affected by the shutdown.
- [Narrator] I wanted
to attend a university
that had an intelligence program.
I wanted to look at problems different.
I wanted to increase my
critical thinking abilities.
AMU offered those avenues to expand.
Obtaining your degree as an adult,
you're actually paying yourself
and investing in yourself
and you can't put a dollar
on it, it's priceless.
It's something that can
never be taken away from you.
- [Narrator] American Military University.
Learn from the leader.
- My next guest has a 12
show Las Vegas residency
this spring at the Colosseum
at Caesar's Palace.
Here performing his classic
song, Your Smiling Face,
please welcome legendary
singer-songwriter James Taylor.
(audience cheers)
("Your Smiling Face" by James Taylor)
♪ Whenever I see your smiling face ♪
♪ I have to smile myself ♪
♪ Because I love you ♪
♪ And when you give me
that pretty little pout ♪
♪ It turns me inside out ♪
♪ Something about you baby ♪
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ Isn't it amazing a man like me ♪
♪ Can feel this way ♪
♪ Tell me how much longer ♪
♪ If it grows stronger every day ♪
♪ Oh no ♪
♪ I thought I was in love
a couple of times before ♪
♪ With the girl next door ♪
♪ But that was long before I met you ♪
♪ Now I'm sure that I won't forget you ♪
♪ And I thank my lucky stars ♪
♪ That you are who you are ♪
♪ And not just another lovely lady ♪
♪ Sent down to break my heart ♪
♪ Isn't it amazing a man like me ♪
♪ Can feel this way ♪
♪ Tell me how much longer ♪
♪ If it grows stronger every day ♪
♪ Oh how much longer ♪
♪ Nobody can tell me that I'm ♪
♪ Doing wrong today ♪
♪ Whenever I see your smile ♪
♪ Nobody can tell me that I'm ♪
♪ Doing wrong not today no ♪
♪ Whenever you shine that
thing my way little one ♪
♪ Oh no no no ♪
♪ No no no no no no ♪
♪ La la la la ♪
♪ Come on come on come on ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ No no no no ♪
♪ La la la la ♪
♪ Nobody gonna turn me round ♪
♪ Nobody gonna put me down ♪
♪ Nobody gonna push me around ♪
♪ Whenever I see your smile ♪
♪ No one can tell me that ooh-wee ♪
♪ I'm doing wrong today ♪
(audience cheers)
- Thank you, James.
- Thank you.
- James Taylor everybody!
(audience cheers)
♪ It's easy at Sheehy ♪
- [Narrator] The shorter the
month, the bigger the savings
during Sheehy's President's
Day Sales Event.
Get your best price fast,
and upfront with Easy Price,
limited time savings are here during our
President's Day Sales Event.
♪ At sheehy.com ♪
- [Narrator] When winter
rears its ugly head,
you can stay in and cozy up to the fire,
or go out
and light one.
(intense music)
Dodge Durango, join the
brotherhood of muscle,
and hurry in for winter deals.
Now get 500 President's Day bonus cash
for a total cash allowance of 2,000
on the 2019 Dodge Durango
SXT all wheel drive.
- You know what's awesome about
having the fastest,
most reliable internet?
All of your kids' friends
want to come over.
You know what's not awesome about having
the fastest, most reliable internet?
All your kids' friends wanna come over.
- [Boy] Would you like a chip?
- Oh honey, that's potpourri.
- Oh, then do you want a potpourri?
- No thanks, I'm driving.
- [Narrator] Get speed, coverage,
and control with Xfinity xFi.
Now that's simple, easy, awesome.
Get started with this
special offer from Xfinity
for 79.99 a month for two years,
plus get DVR service free for a year.
Click, call, or visit a store today.
- [Narrator] My Pacifica
hybrid minivan is so quiet
I could finally hear myself think.
Where could I go with a
566 mile driving range?
Can vegetarians still eat animal crackers?
Another Pacifica, safe choice my friend.
- [Narrator] I bet she's
all super green and healthy.
- [Narrator] Best burger ever!
- [Narrator] During the
President's Day Sales Event,
owners of competitive vehicles purchased
can get 4,250 total cash allowance
on the 2019 Pacifica.
- Thanks Dad, bye.
- Bye.
- [Boy] Hey what's up guys?
- [Narrator] 1979 never knew what hit it.
- Yeah turn it up, turn it up!
- [Narrator] Jiffy Lube came on the scene,
and changed the automotive world.
- We're gonna be out of here in no time.
- Seriously.
- [Narrator] Four decades later,
Jiffy Lube is changing everything, again.
Offering services that
are fast and convenient
using manufacturer recommendations.
- Seriously?
(gasps)
- [Narrator] Jiffy Lube,
you can do more in a jiffy.
♪ It's easy at Sheehy ♪
- [Narrator] The shorter the
month, the bigger the savings
during Sheehy's President's
Day Sales Event.
Find your next vehicle fast
with Easy Search online.
Limited time savings are here during our
President's Day Sales Event.
♪ At sheehy.com ♪
- Goodnight!
(audience cheers)
(upbeat jazz music)