- Leave their bar, and you're toasted
or you hit somebody.
They're coming to find out
where the last place you were was.
And I feel like sometimes, you know,
this is a wake up call.
Do your homework.
- [Joy] Yeah.
- For everybody, don't just
'cause it looks like it's gonna be good
and you think they're gonna be there,
probably they're not gonna be,
so maybe want to save your
money and do something better.
- People lost over $20 million.
- Yeah, it's it's a
lot of dough for folks.
- [Meghan] 26, that's a lot.
- Yeah.
There we are, we'll be back.
(applauding)
- [Announcer] Former
Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz
says he may run for
president as an Independent.
How does he answer critics
who say he'll derail Democrats
and hand Trump a victory?
He's live on The View, next.
- We're doing karaoke later,
and you're gonna sing.
- Jamie, this is your house?
- I know, it's not much, but it's home.
Right kids?
- Kids?
- Papa, papa.
- You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
- Oh yeah.
- This one is tiny like a child.
- Yeah, she is.
Ah, but seriously, it's
good to be surrounded
by what matters most,
a home and auto bundle from Progressive.
- Oh Sweetie, please play for us.
- Oh no, I couldn't.
Okay.
(singing in foreign language)
- My gums are irritated.
I don't have to worry about that, do I?
- Actually you do.
Harmful bacteria lurk
just below the gum line.
- [Announcer] New Crest Gum Detoxify
works below to neutralize
harmful plaque bacteria
and help reverse early gum damage.
Gum Detoxify from Crest.
- [Announcer] People
everywhere are confusing
Quilted Northern for robes.
They're cushiony, comforting,
and add elegance to your home.
But Quilted Northern is not a robe.
It's just really nice toilet paper.
- When I walked through a
snow storm for a cigarette,
that's when I knew I had to quit.
For real this time.
That's why I'm using Nicorette.
- [Announcer] Only
Nicorette Gum has patented
dual-coated technology for great taste
plus intense craving relief.
- Every great why, needs a great how.
(heart beats)
- What about this guy?
- This guy's been through a lot.
(somber music)
- [Announcer] Dogs bring
out the good in us.
Pedigree brings out the good in them.
Feed the good.
- Hi this is Jonathan.
- I'm Karen.
- I'm Lisa.
- [Announcer] Looking
for a real relationship?
- I'm looking for a woman
who's trusting, funny and kind.
- I can't wait to meet
somebody who loves dogs
as much as I do.
- Definitely would like
to meet someone special.
- [Announcer] Check out
Match right now for free.
- [Announcer] Sometimes the
pressures of today's world
can make it tough to
take care of yourself,
but Nature's Bounty has innovative ways
to help you maintain balance,
and help keep you active
and well rested, because hey,
tomorrow's coming up fast.
Nature's Bounty, because
you're better off healthy.
- [Announcer] L'Oreal Paris introduces--
- [Woman] Rouge Signature.
Matte Color Ink,
less texture, more color.
- [Woman] Less excess, more impact.
- [Announcer] All day
matte, bare lip sensation.
Rouge Signature.
Matte Colored Ink, by L'Oreal Paris.
- We're worth it.
- [Announcer] For a nasty
cold, take new DayQuil Severe
with Vicks VapoCOOL.
- [Woman] Man drinks DayQuil.
- [Announcer] And vaporize
it with an intense rush
of Vicks vapors.
- [Woman] Man breathes
easier with Vicks VapoCOOL.
- [Announcer] New DayQuil
Severe with Vicks VapoCOOL.
The daytime coughing, aching, stuffy head,
vaporize your cold, medicine.
- [Announcer] Lunchtime
on Strahan and Sara,
Snoop hangs with Michael,
things got, well, you know.
- You're crazy Mike.
- [Announcer] Plus the Sharks are here.
Strahan and Sara, lunchtime on ABC.
- [Announcer] Stronger is
rebuilding a newborn's heart.
And restoring a father's faith.
It's standing tall after
one surgery, not six.
Stronger is being a typical
kid, despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding it earlier,
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is seeking answers,
and not giving up until you find them.
(lively music)
Because we don't just
want your kids to grow up,
we want them to grow up stronger.
- GEICO makes it easy
to help when you need it
with licensed agents available 24-7.
It's not just easy,
it's having a walrus in goal easy.
(growls)
- It's a walrus.
Ridiculous.
- Yes, nice save big guy.
- Good job, Duncan, way to go.
(growls)
(imitating walrus growl)
- [Announcer] It's not
just easy, it's GEICO easy.
- [Coach] Duncan, stay up, no sleepies.
(doorbell rings)
- [Announcer] Ready to conquer winter?
Then it has to be a Honda SUV.
More capable with an
available turbo charged engine
and real time all wheel drive.
More safety with Honda Sensing,
including a collision mitigation system.
And less getting lost.
Get more this winter with a Honda SUV.
2019's best SUV brand.
Right now, get a 2019 CRV
for just $259 a month.
- Don't settle for less than a Honda.
- We didn't.
- [Announcer] See your
local Honda dealer today.
("World's Gone Crazy" by Mary J. Blige)
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ World's gone crazy ♪
- All right, former
Starbucks chairman and CEO
Howard Schultz was a
hot topic here yesterday
for saying he's seriously
considering running for President
as an Independent (hisses).
- Oh, come on.
- And he's here to tell us right now,
why he wants to do that.
Please welcome author of the new book,
From the Ground Up, Howard Schultz.
- Thank you very much.
(audience applauding)
Thank you.
- So, I am gonna ask you about that
because I think you've
been a lifelong Democrat.
- Yes.
- Are you not sure that your
policies are strong enough
to run as a Democrat?
- Well, I think I would
have to be disingenuous
to run as a Democrat today
but I think the question
that I'm asking myself
and I think many of us
are asking ourselves
is what kind of country
do we want to live in
and right now I think it's clear
that the country we are living
in needs significant change
not only change because of this president.
- [Whoopi] Right.
- But change because of the toxicity
and the lack of compromise of both parties
and we certainly saw that--
(audience applauds)
- [Whoopi] Right.
- And we certainly saw
that over the last month.
The president was responsible
for closing the government
but 800,000 people and their families
were doing everything possible just to eat
and the Democrats as well as Republicans
are responsible for that.
- All right.
- Well, I just want to ask quickly
what are the Dems too left on, you think?
What issues will not divide them?
- Well, I don't know Senator Harris but
listened to her last night
say we should abolish
the insurance industry
as a way to go forward on health care.
That alone would wipe out
millions of jobs of Americans
and that is the kind of extreme policy
that is not a policy that I agree with.
And if you take immigration,
you take health care,
what we have is extremes on both sides
not representing the large
majority of Americans
who don't have a voice
and what I'm saying is
let's give the American people a choice
and what better expression of democracy
and why should we only rely
on Republicans and Democrats
that have displayed not
only the last two years
but for decades, an inability
to do the people's work.
- All right, I'll tell
you why in a second but.
- Okay.
(laughing)
- I want to tell people
about you a little bit
because when I had it over at CNN,
I ran into Howard on the elevator
and I said to him, Howard get me a latte.
He's a Starbucks guy, right?
(laughing)
And I was teasing you.
And I went back to my office
and next thing I know,
he shows up, I have a picture of it,
he shows up with a latte.
Now, that's a great guy,
you know what I mean?
That the CEO of Starbucks
delivers a latte to me.
Very nice and I also like the fact
that you gave insurance to
your part-time employees.
That was really sweet,
I mean that's a little above and beyond.
But, but, and here's the big but.
- Okay.
- Michael Bloomberg has
said to you don't run
and he was thinking of running
but then he did the research
and he found out he couldn't win
so he got out of the race.
The main thing and I said it yesterday
that scares me.
- Yes.
- Is that your entry into this race
will guarantee Trump another four years
and we cannot have that.
You talk about the Democrats
not wanting to negotiate.
They cannot negotiate with a toddler.
If you give him the cookie one day,
the next day he wants another cookie.
So that's not equal on both sides.
They had to play tough, the Democrats,
with him otherwise he will run amok.
Now your entry into the
race pretty much guarantees
that a Republican is going to win.
And I know you're much more--
- Joy, I do not agree with you.
- I know you don't.
- I don't agree with you.
In fact, not only do I not agree with you
but I think if President
Trump runs against
a far left progressive liberal Democrat.
- But what if he runs against Biden?
Biden's a middle of the road guy.
- Biden hasn't come into the race yet.
But just let's finish.
If he runs against a far
left progressive person
who is suggesting 60, 70%
tax increases on the rich
and a health care system
that we can't pay for--
- [Whoopi] I don't know about that.
- President Trump is gonna get reelected.
And all I'm saying is let
me go out to the country
and let the people hear my story.
I grew up in the projects of Brooklyn.
I gave my company
comprehensive health insurance,
equity in the form of stock options,
free college tuition for every employee
and I figured out--
- But you can't do that with a country.
- Well, you can.
- No, listen you, because
this is the same problem
you know who has, when you look at--
When you own your company--
- Yes.
- You can make these changes
as you want them to be.
- Right.
When you have to report to
the Senate and the Congress
and all the 50 million people
that come in the middle,
that's a little bit different
and so, you know, my big problem is
I want people to stand up
for what they believe in
and I think you are
you're saying to people
I don't think you'll hear me
unless I speak to you as an Independent.
I think if you believe
in what you believe in,
then stand up for that as a Democrat
and then change the party
if you feel like that.
As opposed to going elsewhere.
(audience applauds)
That was what I wanted to finish saying.
- Okay.
Can I ask you all one question,
and maybe even the audience?
Does anyone believe the current system,
not only the President,
but the current political
system and our government
is working well on behalf
of the American people?
- Not since Obama was elected, no.
- No.
- I do think it's the
best thing that we have.
- I think that it has to
do with money in campaigns
and money in politics.
And you're a glaring example
that as long as you're a billionaire,
you can run for anything
and my problem with politics right now
is the influence of
money and no shade at you
but you do have to be a billionaire
to run as an Independent.
That's why Michael Bloomberg's
the other example you've given.
- Well, but you can't buy the presidency.
The American people are gonna decide.
But let me just let make one point.
(laughing)
Can I make one point?
- Sure.
- In the last three or
four presidential elections
basically eight battleground
states decided the election.
That's a fact.
- Yeah?
- Now, if an Independent person
were to run for president
and get on the ballot of all 50 states
which if I decide to run,
we will be on the ballot of all 50 states.
For the first time--
- How?
- In almost 40 years, I'll get there.
For the first time in almost 40 years,
every state, every
person's vote, will matter.
It won't be eight states.
It'll be a 50 state race.
- As opposed to the electoral college?
- No, but--
- So, it's a way of circumventing it?
- No, it's not a way of circumventing it,
because we could get to 270
because every state will matter
but the issue that I think--
- Every state does matter.
That's why the Electoral College exists.
And I love the primary.
I love primary politics
and no disrespect to you
but you just went on
Gwyneth Paltrow's podcast.
You're here on The View.
All politics I believe,
should start local.
Why aren't you in New
Hampshire or Iowa, right now?
- You know what I wanna ask though, I.
- [Joy] He's selling a book.
- I know but if you're
running for president,
which I believe you are,
I still believe in the,
sorry Sunny to interrupt you.
I do, I truly believe in it.
And I actually think that like if like,
if you go to New Hampshire
which I've done, as have Abby,
these people take their vote
and they take their first in
the nation status seriously
and the idea that you negate their choice
and I'm not gonna concede that.
I still am fine with
the Electoral College.
- I think you're misunderstanding me.
I'm not saying anything
against the Electoral College.
What I'm saying is, if
it's a 50-state race,
you can get to 270, the
Electoral College applies.
With regard to New Hampshire and Iowa,
watch every Democrat go to those states
and have to be disingenuous
and probably make a false
promise about Fenton Hall
just to be able to get elected
in the primary in those states.
I would have to be
disingenuous as a Democrat
if I ran as a Democrat
because in order to run
as a Democrat today,
you have to fall in line with
free Medicare for everybody,
free, free college for everybody,
a free job for everybody, let me finish.
- That's what you just
said you gave everybody.
- But not free for the for the government
and that totals about $40
trillion on top of the fact
that we are sitting on a $21 trillion debt
in the country today.
We can't afford to do it free
so it has to be a different way.
And the different way is
corporate responsibility
has to fall in line and
do more for their people
and the communities we
serve like Starbucks did
and pharmaceutical companies and lobbyists
that have been paying these politicians,
Democrats and Republicans have to stop
and can you imagine just
imagine for one minute
if an Independent person
could have a mandate
from the country, from the people,
the first one since George Washington,
to finally say to the system
and the special interests
it no longer applies,
that an Independent person
can break the logjam
of this toxicity that
exists in an unwillingly--
- [Joy] But that's where--
- Hold on one second, we're almost done.
We're gonna be talking some more
with Howard Schultz when we come back.
(audience applauding)
- [Meghan] I'm sorry.
(music crescendos)
- I can do more to lower my A1C.
- Because my body can still
make it's own insulin.
- And I take Trulicity once a week
to activate my body to release it,
like it's supposed to.
Trulicity is not insulin.
It starts acting in my
body from the first dose
and continues to work
when I need it, 24/7.
- [Announcer] Trulicity is an injection
to improve blood sugar in
adults with Type 2 Diabetes
when used with diet and exercise.
Don't use it as the first
medicine to treat Diabetes
or if you Type 1 Diabetes
or Diabetic Ketoacidosis.
Don't take Trulicity if you or your family
have medullary thyroid cancer,
you're allergic to Trulicity,
or have Multiple Endocrine
Neoplasia syndrome type 2.
Stop Trulicity and call
your doctor right away
if have symptoms of a
serious allergic reaction,
a lump or swelling in your
neck or severe stomach pain.
Serious side effects may
include pancreatitis.
Taking Trulicity with a
sulfonylurea or insulin,
increases your low blood sugar risk.
Common side effects
include nausea, diarrhea,
vomiting, abdominal pain
and decreased appetite.
Do you.