- Not again.
- [Announcer] Let CET
help you get the training
you need for the job you want.
There are no semesters or quarters here.
You can start almost any time.
Go from learning to earning.
CET is approved to train veterans,
offers financial aid and
job placement assistance.
Lots of programs to choose from.
Enroll today, start tomorrow.
Call CET and change your life.
- [Announcer] Buy one, take one is back
starting at just $12.99 at Olive Garden.
Join us for a new favorite today.
Then bring one home for tomorrow on us.
Buy one, take one,
for a limited time only at Olive Garden.
- [Narrator] Microwave breakfasts.
- [Dr. Oz] Omelet cups,
burritos, and egg muffins.
- [Narrator] Fast, easy.
- When it comes to frozen food,
breakfast foods are queen.
- [Narrator] But are
they really good for you?
- Or are they just junk food in disguise?
- [Narrator] Plus, fat shamers.
- [Woman] I can't sit here
because they're both so big.
- [Narrator] Caught on tape.
- [Man] She's eating too much chocolate.
- [Woman] Why are you
insulting me about my weight?
- [Narrator] Coming up next.
(intense music)
(upbeat music)
- Y'all ready for season 10?
- [Crowd] Yeah!
- I love you, Dr. Oz.
(audience cheers and applause)
- Today, an investigation
into a giant shift
happening in your frozen food aisle.
The food industry is
offering an unprecedented
number of microwavable frozen
breakfast food options,
including your favorites,
breakfast sandwiches,
delicious looking omelet cups,
burritos and egg muffins,
all hot and ready in minutes.
Many even claim to be
healthier, but are they,
or are they just junk food in disguise?
Investigator and mom of
two, Mara Schiavocampo,
put many of these options to the test
in the best food lab there
is, her own busy kitchen.
- Okay so, I'm shopping
for breakfast sandwiches.
I can't remember the last time
I bought a breakfast sandwich.
So this should be interesting.
Hey quesadilla.
Do you wanna try these for breakfast?
- Um, what are they?
- [Mara] It's a breakfast
sandwich made on a waffle.
It's bacon, egg, and cheese.
- I don't really like eggs or cheese,
but I could try with something else.
Maybe just bacon?
- [Mara] So, this is
what I ended up getting.
We have two different English muffins.
They are different.
This one is like on a waffle
and this is a breadless
egg cup which I am very excited about.
(audience applause)
- Mara, be honest, was
that the best assignment
you have ever been given?
- You know, any assignment
that involves tasting food,
I'm in, sign me up for it.
- [Dr. Oz] And your daughter's already an
investigative reporter.
- She's very discerning, yeah.
You know, breakfast is a
really hard meal for me.
I was really happy to get this assignment
because this is tough for me.
I'm a low carb eater.
So I'm always looking for
portable, low carb options,
and with my kids, I'm
looking for alternatives
to the staples that are high sugar,
high carb, like cereal and pancakes.
So this could change things in my house.
- And how big have these
products become now,
these microwavable breakfasts?
- When it comes to frozen food,
breakfast foods are doing so well.
Really it's for two reasons.
One is millennials.
So, 82% of millennials say that this
is a good option for their
kids and case in point,
I agree with that completely.
The other one is the keto crowd.
Keto is huge right now.
They're looking for low carb options.
Those two things are
driving this industry.
- Yeah, they use, the bun is actually egg.
- And it looks so delicious.
- It does look good.
All right, that's a start.
So we asked food scientist, Taylor,
and he's a fanatic, by the
way, about breakfast foods.
Taylor Wallace to be here to break down
exactly how microwavable
breakfasts are made.
Let's start with the prime
ingredient of all, the egg.
Is there a real egg in these
microwavable breakfasts?
Crack the egg for me.
- So actually, yes.
Many of these products, the
main ingredient is a whole egg.
Now, also in these
products, you're gonna see
some of your other normal culprits,
different food additives.
Now, they might look scary
but they're all in there
for a functional purpose, right?
So for instance, it looks scary.
Xanthan gum, that's just a dietary fiber
that we add to food.
We add it to eggs because we
don't want the egg to crumble
when you bite into it
and fall into your lap.
Modified corn starch, that just provides
a little bit of texture to the product.
And then you have all
these different flavors
and you might ask, well
why not just add butter?
Because butter oxidizes and
makes the product go stale.
So, instead, we add these flavors that
won't oxidize and produce a bad taste.
- Well you just expressed a bias.
I love that it's a real egg.
I sorta wish I didn't have to
add all these things in there
but I know you guys
have other technologies.
We have a way of making the
frozen, microwavable breakfast
flavorful and locking in that flavor
and it has to do with this,
and you're a flavor scientist,
so what does this have to do with flavor?
- So, there's two main things
that you have to worry about
in products like egg sandwiches.
One is water because we know
water makes things go bad,
and two is oxygen because
oxygen oxidizes things.
So what do we do?
We freeze the water because
frozen water can't do much
and then we add nitrogen to
the bag or to the package.
So, very similar to what
you see in potato chips.
If you buy a bag of potato
chips with all the air inside,
that's nitrogen.
When you open then bag,
then the oxygen comes in.
You leave it out for a
day and it goes stale.
The same thing happens
with egg sandwiches.
- All right, so let's take
a look at different types of
frozen breakfasts that we
find at the grocery store.
I took that list that you just got Mara,
that treasure trove and I split it out,
and I know that there's a big keto move.
So explain how people
have hacked that system.
- Yeah, so just as a reminder, it's very,
very high fat, very low carb.
So when you take a look at these
traditional breakfast sandwiches here,
these are not gonna be an option
for keto followers because of the bread.
But when you look over
here, this is really
a game changer if you're keto devotee.
They have made the bread out of eggs.
So this is breadless.
It's essentially,
(audience applause)
two egg patties--
- I saw that, I wasn't
sure if that was real.
- It's real, it's eggs,
it is high protein.
It is extremely low carb.
- So egg bun.
- Yeah, so this is the industry
responding to that demand.
They have heard loud and clear
what low carb dieters want.
- All right, so seven grams of carbs.
How do the rest of your options compare?
- Yeah so you can see
it's a big difference.
So the English muffin
option, 28 grams of carbs,
so I've never been good
at math but I think
that's four times the
amount, right, roughly.
- You're better than you say.
It's exactly four times it.
- And here we have the
croissant, 27 grams,
pretty much the same.
The biscuit, which to me looks like
the most delectable, delicious one.
- [Dr. Oz] I think that's
a pretty good deal.
- Oh my goodness, I'm working
hard not to take a bite.
- But this is intriguing to me.
Flatbread's a good idea.
- Flatbread is a great idea.
You see that it is the
lowest carb of all of them
but still much higher
than the breadless one.
- Now you tasted these and you had
that discerning of you taste as well.
How did this breadless version do?
- It was absolutely delicious.
I did not miss the bread at all.
But I did have to wonder,
is that too much protein?
Am I overdoing it?
- I looked into it, I
think the protein's okay.
The bigger concern for me is salt.
Sometimes in order to make it flavorful,
because when you freeze things it
doesn't taste the same always.
They can have more salt than you want.
So just take a look at that.
But overall I was impressed
that you had this many options.
But I wanna go to our
audience member here,
'cause the next microwavable
frozen breakfast investigation
had to do with the crustless quiches.
There's no carbs in a crustless quiche.
Do I have this right?
- [Lisa] Yes.
(laughing)
- Well I wanna do a thing.
Compare these two and see
if you taste the difference.
Mara, you can go do it as well, here.
- Oh thank you, I thought you'd never ask.
- Exactly.
I figured you eat them all
at home before you got here.
I'm gonna reveal something
to you in a second,
but these are not quite made the same way.
So, which do you like more of these?
- This one's much better.
- Much better?
- Mhmm.
All right, so I'm just gonna
reveal something to you.
One of these is actually
homemade, by yours truly.
And the other one was made in a store.
This was made by us.
- [Lisa] Nice job, Dr. Oz.
- [Mara] Oh wow.
- This is the store bought one.
I only point it out because
this didn't take a ton of time.
I think most people prefer it,
but I get why you don't do it.
It's a lack of time.
Does this taste good enough that if
you didn't have time to
make that on your own
you'd still be okay with it?
- Yeah I'd be okay with it.
- All right, so it works.
- Yeah, it's a great option.
- You pick and choose what you want,
I don't think it's quite the
same as making it yourself
but it's probably good enough for most,
especially busy moms out there.
How do they compare nutritionally?
- So it's actually, there's
a lot of good news here.
These have, the store bought ones,
are real egg or egg base,
which is just basically liquid egg.
Now they do have other things added in
because they do have to live on a shelf,
they do have to be frozen.
But for the most part it is
very close to the real thing.
You can feel good about eating them
and giving them to your kids.
- Show off at home, Lisa.
All right, me, one last stop.
We invested frozen microwave
breakfast burritos.
Taylor these have been getting
a lot of criticism over the years,
but they seem to be making a comeback.
- Right, you know, when I was a kid,
it was like these things
are terrible, right?
I mean they're mushy
and gooey and not great.
Food scientists have this down to an art
and now, just like over
there, they taste fantastic.
And not only that, there's
vegetarian options,
there's farm to table options.
We've got something for everybody.
- So you still wanna
watch the sodium on these,
especially if you got pressure issues.
We always say make bacon a special food,
so you don't want to have
that every day either.
Maybe twice a week kinda thing.
When we come back we show you a brand new
microwavable breakfast that allows you
to use your own fresh egg.
Is it the best of both worlds?
We'll find out when we come back.
(audience applause)
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Confessions of shoplifters.
- Moms who seem to have a
really strong moral compass
have this dirty little secret.
- It happens every time
I walk into a store.
- [Narrator] Plus, Pamela Smart,
convicted of conspiracy to commit murder.
- The prosection painted this idea
that this was a black widow
out for revenge and money.
- [Narrator] But did she really get her
15 year old lover to pull the trigger?
- Why isn't she crying?
Her husband's dead.
- [Narrator] All new Oz.
- [Announcer] Macy's black
Friday in July is here.
Get spectacular savings store wide,
plus an extra 25% off with
your coupon or Macy's card.
And there's more.
Everyone gets free shipping at Macys.com,
on every order, with no minimum.
Today and tomorrow only at Macy's.
- [Announcer] You're gonna do your thing,
and no period is gonna slow you down.
With Tampax, you get
protection that moves with you
for total comfort.
Choose Pearl for your chill,
Pocket for your moves,
and Active for your hustle.
Do your thing with Tampax.
- [Announcer] Both men
and women have trouble
sleeping these days.
So Alteril contains three different
effective sleep compounds that work
on different parts of the
brain for restful sleep
for both men and women.
If you have trouble sleeping, try Alteril.
Alteril is not like other sleep aids
because Alteril contains three
unique sleeping compounds
each designed to work on
different parts of the brain
for fast, restful sleep.
Alteril is like three
sleeping pills in one.
Alteril, for fast restful sleep.
- Selling your house?
We'll buy it as is, handle all repairs,
and there's never a fee.
Get to life's next step even faster
with peace of mind and
cash in your pocket.
♪ Express home buyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
- Ooh, a tire commercial.
Turn it up!
- [Announcer] Right now at NTB,
buy three tires get one free,
with paid standard installation.
Save on top brands like
Good Year, Continental,
Cooper, Nitto, and more.
Buy three tires, get one free at NTB.
- That's all you need.
- [Announcer] Get beautiful
new floors right now
with Luna's incredible 70% off sale.
That's carpet, laminate
and even hardwood 70%.
You'll get professional installation
and can be confident with Luna's exclusive
love your floors promise.
Transform your home
with an amazing 70% off
carpet, laminate, and hard wood.
Reserve your free in-home
appointment at luna.com or call.
♪ 877 241 LUNA ♪
- I used to be a one cheese operation,
but me and crunchy here make a great team.
We even finish each other's...
You're supposed to say sentences.
- Sentences.
- Well not now.
- Delicious new Babybel
cheese and crackers.
- Saved it.
- The only thing that
I would do differently,
the only thing,
I should've called Express
Home Buyers sooner.
♪ Express Home Buyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
(audience applause)
- If you have ever tried to make an omelet
and this happens, right, you're not alone.
Guess what, restaurants, the
best places in the world,
using making an omelet
as the ultimate test
of a chef's true skill.
So I didn't pass this time,
but I'm getting better.
I can cover it up.
I can stitch this back together again.
I got the stick knowledge.
Anyway, today we're investigating
a brand new shortcut
turning omelets into
a weekday quickie meal
using your own microwave.
These are called omelets in a cup.
Now food scientist Taylor Wallace is here
to help us figure out
what's really in these.
There's too many kinds
of omelets in a cup.
Break them up for us.
(audience applause)
- Okay, so your first kind, go
ahead and open that package,
and what you'll see, it's
got everything inside.
So you've got your little
vegetables and meat.
And then you have a liquid egg,
so go on and check it out.
And a liquid egg is
basically the same thing
that you buy in the grocery store
in those milk carton-like jugs.
It's just been pasteurized
a little bit more
than the old way to prevent
bacteria from growing.
- So pour it in here?
- Yep, so pour it right in.
You can pop it in the microwave
and you're ready to go basically.
- [Dr. Oz] Put my fixings
in there, I'm good to go.
- [Taylor] Absolutely.
- It's so easy, so simple.
So how is yours different?
- So the second one, this is for consumers
that prefer their products
a little less processed.
So we charge 'em the same price
but don't add the egg,
you have to add your own.
- You're kidding me, it's the same price?
- Right, and instead of the
egg you have to add your own
and it's not a liquid egg.
So if you see, you've got the cheese,
the vegetables, the meat in there,
same thing as in your other product.
- Break the egg.
You have to break it on plastic.
Oh my goodness.
Here, break it over here,
and put it in the pan, there.
All right.
That's it.
And you add the goodies in there.
- [Taylor] Then you add the stuff,
mix it up, and there you go.
(audience applause)
- I gotta say I'm impressed.
This is actually so close to
what I would normally wanna do,
I'd probably think about this.
- Right, and like Mara said,
they're very close to
the normal food product
that you would cook in your kitchen.
Got a little bit of additives in there
to help prevent mold
growth or bacteria growth,
but overall it's the same thing.
- A food scientist is happy, I'm happy.
All right, and the price
you mentioned is the same.
- Yeah the price, I
mentioned, is about $3 a pack.
So great for someone
like a college student
or somebody like you and
I that are on the go.
Might not wanna feed
the whole family with it
'cause that gets kind of expensive.
But great on the go.
- I gotta say, as I look at these...
(static)
(alarm sounds)
- [Announcer] This is a statement from
the National Weather Service.
For the following country,
District of Columbia,
and the following counties in Maryland,
Montgomery, and Prince George's.
The National Weather Service
in Sterling, Virginia,
has issued a flood warning
for the District of Columbia,
Montgomery County in Central Maryland,
Prince George's County
in Central Maryland,
until 6 p.m at 12:40 p.m.
Reporting gages and reports
from emergency managers
indicate flooding is ongoing across
portions of Montgomery,
Prince George's County,
and the District of Columbia.
With heavy rain now over, a
flood warning has been issued
to replace the flash flood warning
that has been in effect.
Some locations that will
experience flooding include
Arlington, Alexandria,
Germantown, Rockville,
Bethesda, Gaithersburg, Bowie, Clinton,
Olney, College Park, Fort Washington,
Greenbelt, Langley Park, Beltsville,
Fort Hunt, Damascus, Forestville,
Lowes Island, Largo, and Coral Hills.
Turn around.
Don't drown when
encountering flooded roads.
Most flood deaths occur in vehicles.
- Foods can be doing to your brain.
- [Announcer] Why not
take the whole family
out for a geological thrill?
Only at Luray Caverns.
What will you discover?
- You just can't trust
the internet these days.
Luckily, I discovered Nord VPN.
Thanks to Nord VPN I
feel so safe online now.
I just click and let Nord VPN do the rest.
Who would have thought
it takes just a click
to keep the hackers away?
(melodic music)
- So Kim, you going for a big
drive safe and save discount?
- Yep, using the app,
I've been quite vigilant.
- Sharon says step on it,
the meeting's started.
- Okay write her back, dear Sharon,
don't mess with my discount.
- Faster mommy, I gotta
go to the bathroom.
- I do too honey but we're gonna hold it
for mommy's discount.
Easy, easy.
- But you're in labor.
- Don't mess with my discount!
(clears throat)
- [Announcer] Get a discount up to 30%
with drive safe and save from State Farm.
- [Announcer] Looking for that great job
but lack the experience?
- Not again.
- [Announcer] Let CET help
you get the training you need
for the job you want.
There are no semesters or quarters here.
You can start almost anytime.
Go from learning to earning.
CET is approved to train veterans,
offers financial aid, and
job placement assistance.
Lots of programs to choose from.
Enroll today, start tomorrow.
Call CET and change your life.
- Spending so much of
your life underwater,
you learn to talk to yourself.
What you don't learn is
how to talk to others.
The black line on the bottom
of the pool never talks back.
If I could go back in time I would tell
my younger self to open up,
and to work with a professional therapist.
Therapy can dramatically change your life.
It helped me a lot, so you
should try it for yourself.
- [Announcer] Get $50 off your first month
of Talk Space therapy
with coupon Michael 50.
- Brought to you by Talk
Space, therapy for all.
- [Announcer] Around
here, even a little rain
makes us downright giddy.
That's because we've seen it do
some pretty spectacular things.
See for yourself at Luray Caverns.
What will you discover?
(microwave beeping)
- I know,
(audience applause)
did you start to salivate at that sound?
You start to think about food when
the beep starts with your microwave.
Millions of you rely on
quick microwave meals
because it's a quick lunch or
ready in minutes hot dinner.
But can you get addicted to
these fast food frozen foods?
How does your freezer look?
Does it look like this?
Someone in our audience is the owner of
this stocked freezer full
of those microwave meals
and is being turned in for their obsession
with microwave meals.
Please welcome Angela, who's turning in
her best friend Suella.
- Hi Dr. Oz.
(laughing)
- Suella, you didn't know
this was happening did you?
- No, no.
I think I'm fine.
- [Dr. Oz] You think you're fine.
What is the issue here?
- She has a problem.
She has a very big problem.
- And that's a real photo of her freezer.
- Yes.
- [Dr. Oz] And how often is she eating
microwave frozen food?
- All the time.
Breakfasts, lunch, snack.
- I'm busy.
- No, it's no.
- I really love it.
- No.
- [Dr. Oz] Well what do
you love about it so much?
- Well they have healthy
ones, I eat Lean Cuisine,
I like hot pockets sometimes
when I'm really in a rush.
So you know, easy is convenient.
- What do you think about
your friend's concern
over your perceived addiction
towards microwave fast food?
- I don't know what her concern is.
- You don't know my concern?
- No.
- You send me coupons, you
wanna buy things off Ebay.
It's microwavable food.
No, you go to the dollar store,
you go to all of the stores.
No, no, no, it's too much.
- Pot pies, really good.
- Let's just talk about,
come on up here a little bit Suella.
We got a little discussion.
I understand the allure of frozen meals,
but in reality, there's
something that's really addictive
in these foods that makes
them so desirous for us.
- And they taste good.
- So Mark Schatzker, food
journalist extraordinaire,
and a real expert in the area,
he's made a taste test
for us that you and I
are gonna be participants in.
But you gotta tell the truth though.
- All right.
- So take us, what are we gonna taste
and what kind of an
organization do you have here?
- Okay we got three lasagnas.
The first one is fresh
lasagna, we made this,
this is like what you'd make at home.
This is also lasagna
we made but not fresh.
We froze it, and then we reheated it.
- Mm.
That fresh is good.
Keep going, I'm moving along here.
- And then we got, this is
the microwavable lasagna
like you'd buy at the supermarket.
- [Dr. Oz] This is the microwave here.
- [Mark] There'll be
something interesting here.
- That is good.
That is really good.
- Tell me what you like about it.
- You should have this.
You'd like it.
- Yeah it tastes real good.
- Okay so there's something
really interesting.
- This is actually better than the fresh.
- Better than fresh.
Something really
interesting happening here.
So this is another tale
of taste bud trickery.
This is where it's in the flavor.
It's in how they created this experience
of lasagna in a frozen
food where we're gonna
find something interesting.
- Let's uncover the anatomy
of a microwave meal.
How do they actually pull that off?
'Cause I do think, like
you, that definitely tastes
better than the frozen stuff
that you made yourself.
What do they do differently?
So the first issue is preservatives.
Mark, what kind are we talking about?
- Okay so yeah, one thing
they do to get that flavor,
they use synthetic flavorings.
We've talked about that before,
but that's how they jack up that flavor.
We also see a lot of
the same guilty suspects
that we see in other processed foods.
There's polysorbate 80,
that's a bulking agent,
that makes the sauce
taste nice and smooth.
There's something called
potassium bromate,
that's a dough additive.
It's actually illegal in some countries.
And then we have sodium nitrite.
Now we've talked about that--
- [Dr. Oz] It's illegal in some countries?
- It's illegal.
And it's in our frozen foods.
- So these are theoretical concerns,
but next issue is a real concern,
which is sugar.
And how much sugar...
Actually why would you
even add sugar to lasagna?
There's already pasta in there.
- Well because, as we saw,
the flavor takes a beating.
So what's an easy way to
jack that flavor back up?
Just dump in some sugar.
And you're gonna be shocked at how much.
We found one frozen entree that had
29 grams of sugar in a serving.
- Suella, do you hear that?
29 grams.
- Okay, it gets worse, 'cause
guess how big the serving is.
This big.
It's only half.
Most people think, they pull
it out of their microwave
and they think I get
to eat the whole thing.
- Yes.
- Well then you're
getting 58 grams of sugar.
That's the sugar that's in two candy bars.
So who would ever thinking
I'm nuking my dinner,
there's two candy bars
worth of sugar in there?
It's crazy.
- So a lot of sugar, and there's another
hidden source of carbs.
Modified starch.
Which I don't even know what...
What do you modify starch to do?
- Yeah modified starch, what is it?
Well it's there to get rid
of some of the problems
that you get when you reheat frozen foods,
so you don't get those puddles of water,
so that it holds its shape.
But it's essentially
carbohydrates that have no flavor.
So you're getting carbs in your tummy
that you don't taste on the way down,
and I think that's where the worry is.
- So stay with Mark for a sec,
I'm gonna explain to
everybody what happens
to your brain while you're having
all these empty carbs
that are hidden from you.
You got the brain here, you got you there.
Take a bite out of one of these meals,
and what ends up happening is you begin
to fall in love with
it, begin to crave it.
Then what happens, your blood
sugar starts to spike up.
When the blood sugar goes up,
dopamine is released from your brain
which makes you really happy, smiley.
We all know that, right, our comfort food.
But then, over time, your blood
sugar falls back down again,
and you crave that high you just had.
So your low blood sugar levels
cause an increased appetite, right,
you eat more food because the time
seems like it's the right to do.
And the next thing you know you eat more
of those frozen meals
that you've been craving
and feeling okay about doing it.
So Mark, you say in addition to this,
which is sort of like
a chemical addiction,
there's a psychological addiction
these microwave meals can cause.
- Yeah, so we've seen
this interaction before.
You got things like
foods with a lot of sugar
and flavoring makes it compulsive,
makes it really delicious in the moment,
hard to stop eating.
So I think there's a lot of ways
these get us eating too much.
- So don't be a killjoy here.
If we're gonna eat our microwave,
'cause I think Suella, who's
nervously laughing now,
is probably gonna still
eat some of the microwaves
that are in her freezer.
Give us some tact and some hacks.
- Okay so one thing is to
look at the ingredient list,
'cause they're not all the same.
The ingredients that come at
the beginning of the list,
there's more of them.
So look for the good things.
If it's a broccoli
pasta, look for broccoli
at the beginning of the ingredient list.
If it's at the very end,
that means there's not much,
and if you don't see it at
all, be worried about that.
- So Suella, I need your verdict here.
Your friend, me, Professor
Shasker next to us,
seems to think you're
probably better served
to eat your microwave
meals a little differently.
What do you think?
- I don't think I'll do it every day now.
I think I'll do it like maybe twice,
maybe three times a week.
Slowly process on my addiction on it.
But thank you for the advice.
- Schatzker, you're having an impact.
Nicely done, thank you for saying that.
We'll be right back.
(audience applause)
(upbeat music)
Shocking updates on the house of horrors.
Why would parents torture
their own children?
Louise Turpin's sister reveals
their intimate prison conversations.
Any expression of remorse?
An Oz True Crime investigation.
That's coming up on Wednesday.
Closed caption sponsorship
brought to you by.
- When I showed my mom the DNA results,
it made her feel proud.
Ancestry specifically showed the regions
that my family was from.
- [Announcer] New
features, greater details,
richer stories.
Get your DNA kit today at Ancestry.com.
- When you're passionate about something,
anything is possible.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Window Nation
brings the perfect fit
for your home, and your wallet,
with buy one window get one free.
Our best deal of the year gets even better
with no down payment, no payments,
and no interest for 12 months.
Call Window Nation today
or visit WindowNation.com.
- After my car accident,
I didn't know that
a lawyer would help deal
with all my medical bills.
- I didn't know I could also get money
for pain and suffering.
- I didn't know the insurance company
wasn't going to give me
the settlement I deserved.
- We do know.
At Saiontz and Kirk we know injury law,
and we know how to get you
the most money possible.
- Clients of Saiontz
and Kirk have collected
over a billion dollars.
- When you need a lawyer,
you have a lawyer.
- Call 1-800-LAWYERS or
visit YouHaveALawyer.com.
If you have a phone, you have a lawyer.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] From new love,
to lifelong friends,
moments together call for
America's family favorite.
Lipton, live alive.
- [Announcer] Get in for
lunch now, at Olive Garden.
With lunch duos starting at 6.99.
Choose a favorite, like lasagna,
or all new pasta bowls,
like shrimp scampi.
Paired with unlimited soup
or salad and breadsticks.
Get never ending value
for lunch at Olive Garden.
- Are you looking for a hassle free
simple way to sell your home as is?
It doesn't matter if you're
downsizing your home,
have fallen behind on
repairs or your mortgage.
Get an offer on your home
in as little as 10 minutes
with House Buyers of America.
We buy houses directly.
There's no middle men, no commissions,
there's no need to deal
with real estate agents,
repairs, inspections and renovations.
Give us a call today.
We're A+ rated with the
Better Business Bureau.
House Buyers of America,
real estate made real easy.
- [Announcer] Window Nation
brings the perfect fit
for your home, and your wallet,
with buy one window get one free.
Our best deal of the year gets even better
with no down payment, no payments,
and no interest for 12 months.
Call Window Nation today
or visit WindowNation.com.
- [Announcer] Weeknights on Me TV.
Watch MASH at seven, Andy at eight,
and Gomer Pyle at nine.
You can find Me TV on
broadcast channel 5.3,
Comcast 196, Cox 804, Verizon FiOS 489,
Atlantic Broadband 157
and other providers.
- We're back with our investigation
into public fat shaming.
Would you know what to
do if it happened to you?
What about if it came from the one person
you trust the most, your own doctor?
According to one study,
about half of women,
half, say they've been
shamed by a physician,
with weight being one of the top reasons.
Latoya says she was fat
shamed by her doctor,
who ignored her pain symptoms.
After feeling ill, Rebecca
says her doctor told her
to lose weight, but turns
out her health issues
were not a result of her size.
It was actually cancer.
So Rebecca, let's talk about your case,
it's pretty serious.
So you go to the doctor,
you're not feeling well,
how did the physicians
respond to the observations
you were making about your own body?
- Yeah so a lot of times it
was very much a dismissal.
It was kind of a dismissal of symptoms,
over and over and over again.
Just a well basically if you just lost
a little bit of weight you'd be fine.
If you just lost a bit of
weight you could breathe better.
We don't really know what's going on
but if you just lot a bit of weight
everything will be okay.
- So after three years,
three years everybody,
of looking around, you
finally got a diagnosis.
What was really happening
inside your body?
- I had a tumor in my left
main stem bronchus in my lung,
and it had kind of killed
the bottom half of my lung
and they had to take
the whole left lung out.
- In part 'cause it
took three years I think
to figure out what was going on.
- Yeah.
- What was it like when
you finally realized
you actually had a life
threatening problem
that was causing this and not
an issue with your weight,
which you never thought was
the problem to begin with?
- It was the first time that like I had
finally gotten a diagnosis and I had spent
so much time trying to figure
out what was wrong with me,
and then somebody finally told
me that something was wrong,
and it was just so freeing to realize
that there was something
that was actually there,
that like no I'm not just fat,
something is wrong in this body.
- So I wish you were
the only person who felt
the way you have stated you felt,
'cause it turns out that obese patients
are 65% more likely than others to have
significant undiagnosed
medical conditions.
We write it off, say it's something else.
And sometimes it is the
weight that's the problem,
but oftentimes it's not.
Are you feeling okay now?
- Yeah I've been cancer free since 2012.
- [Dr. Oz] Good for you.
(audience applause)
Good for you.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
- Latoya, let's talk about your story.
Also an example of doctors
overlooking a real diagnosis.
What happened?
- Well in my case I've been in pain
for the past two decades, since I started
my menstruation when I was about 10 or 11.
All I can remember is
feeling this crippling
paralyzing pain every time
my menzies would come about.
When I went to the doctor initially it was
well how about we give
you some birth control?
When I started gaining, like I wanna say
I started gaining weight,
particularly after I had my son,
it was automatically shifted
to it has to be your weight.
- So your doctors actually finally
found the real diagnosis right?
What was going on?
- My real diagnosis was that I was
diagnosed with endometriosis.
And that wasn't found until
I miscarried several times,
like over, I stopped
counting after four times.
- Oh I'm sorry.
- And it's something that so many people
brush off as it's nothing.
I find that's the issue in a lot of things
in reproductive health.
- Well the reason I'm passionate about
this topic of fat
shaming is because it can
embarrass people and people can do
bad things to themselves
because they're shamed by.
But we also miss the real diagnosis,
which is a much more obvious
way that we hurt people.
Now I should share, Latoya's about to run
her 17th marathon in three weeks.
(audience applause)
So you didn't get held
back, neither of you did.
What is your message to doctors
who are too easily writing off symptoms
to their patients being overweight?
- Actually listen to your patients.
Be patient with your patients.
Essentially, don't just brush it off
or just look at them and then
try to give them a diagnosis.
Actually do the work, look into it,
do blood tests, which I've had,
which proved that I
didn't have some of these
things that they thought that I had.
Actually listen to us, because
when you don't listen to us
then we have a distrust, we have a worry,
and a real fear that nobody
is going to take us serious.
It makes people not want
to actually come to you
and we essentially go to you to trust you,
so just listen to us and know that
this is not all in our heads.
We know our bodies more than anybody else.
- Thank you for sharing
your story with us.
We'll be right back.
(audience applause)
(upbeat music)
Up next, fat shaming caught on tape.
The videos you have to see to believe.
Find out what one woman
kicked off a flight.
- Everyone wants to buy houses these days,
but whom can you trust?
Call Express Home Buyers.
Thousands of home owners have trusted us
to buy their house the hassle free way.
♪ Express Home Buyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
(banging)
- [Announcer] Appliance shopping,
shouldn't be painful.
Come to Bray and Scarff,
where factory trained appliance experts
give you the personal
attention you deserve.
Our July 4th sale has been extended.
Get the lowest prices of the season
on GE Profile packages.
Plus, this GE french door
refrigerator now 1999,
in stainless, slate, or black slate.
Shop local at Bray and Scarff,
where it doesn't cost more to get more.
- [Announcer] At Pro
Plan we believe nutrition
is full of possibilities
to improve your pet's life.
We're redefining what nutrition can do,
because the possibility of a longer life
and a healthy life is the
greatest possibility of all.
Purina Pro Plan, nutrition that performs.
- [Announcer] No matter your plans,
there's a Cox internet plan for you.
Starting at 29.99 a
month for up to 10 megs.
Plus, panoramic wifi blankets your home
with fast, reliable internet.
Cox has fast one gig speeds everywhere.
Super fast speeds for those things
you just can't live without.
Get internet starting
at just 29.99 a month
for up to 10 megs.
Call today to get the internet
plan that fits your life.
Cox internet.
- [Announcer] Buy one take one is back,
starting at just 12.99 at Olive Garden.
Join us for a new favorite today,
then bring one home for tomorrow, on us.
Buy one, take one, for a limited
time only at Olive Garden.
- [Announcer] Looking for that great job
but lack the experience?
- Not again.
- [Announcer] Let CET help
you get the training you need
for the job you want.
There are no semesters or quarters here,
you can start almost any time.
Go from learning to earning.
CET is approved to train veterans,
offers financial aid and
job placement assistance.
Lots of programs to choose from.
Enroll today, start tomorrow.
Call CET and change your life.
- The only thing that
I would do differently,
the only thing, I should have called
Express Home Buyers sooner.
♪ Express Home Buyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
- [Female] Oh my goodness,
I don't know I'm gonna
do this for the next four hours.
This is just impossible
because they're squishing me.
Like friggin', it's just unbelievable.
At least they'll keep me warm.
Find me a window, get me out of here.
I can't breathe, I'm so squished.
Well I eat salad, okay.
I can't sit here because
they're both so big.
- It's pretty awkward, huh?
That was a small taste of what got
that passenger kicked off a recent flight.
She called her seat mates
big pigs among other things.
Today we're exposing fat
shaming caught on tape.
Strangers bullying and
verbally abusing others
because of their weight.
It's a malicious and
disturbing online trend.
- She's eating too much chocolate.
- [Dr. Oz] Fat shaming videos.
- Why are you insulting
me about my weight?
A car full of men stopped
in the middle of a busy road
just so they can roll down their window
and say eat that ice
cream you fat (bleep).
- [Female] Oh my
goodness, I don't know how
I'm gonna do this for the next four hours.
This is just impossible
because they're squishing me.
- [Dr. Oz] Unrestrained
and hurtful comments
shared in posts.
- [Female] Well I eat salad, okay.
- [Dr. Oz] Are leaving
people outraged and shocked.
- [Female] Can you find her another seat?
'Cause I will not be verbally abused.
- What if I had been in such a place
that you saying that to me had made me
go home and kill myself?
- [Dr. Oz] Hurt feelings,
some show no mercy.
- When you wanna dance
around in your skin tight
leotards with your fat rolls hanging out,
and saying you should love me for
my personality not my
body, and you're promoting
laziness and eating unhealthy,
all of a sudden everyone in this world
has got a (bleep) excuse
why they can't be healthy.
- [Dr. Oz] Here, former
Playboy play mate Dani Mathers
seems to have taken fat
shaming to the extreme,
posting this picture of a naked woman
with the comment if I can't unsee this
then you can't either.
- [Female] You're abusing women.
- [Female] I can't sit
here because they're both
so big on left and right.
I can't even sit here.
- [Male] You should be
ashamed of yourself, madam.
What you're dong is so terrible,
you should be ashamed of yourself.
- [Female] Why don't you sit
in between those two pigs?
- [Female] Kiss my fat (bleep) okay.
- Looking at these videos,
you have to ask yourself
what drives people to such hatred?
Norma, the woman who
recorded that viral video
of her seat mate publicly fat shaming her,
joins me now.
First off, thank you
for coming to the show.
- Oh thank you for having me, Dr. Oz.
- Let's go back to what happened
when you first got to your seat.
- Getting comfortable,
seated at the window seat,
realizing that this woman
that was coming into
the middle seat was having a bad day.
She wasn't a happy person.
Verbally saying negative things
and making it a little uncomfortable.
- And how did it make you feel when you
appreciated what she
was really getting at?
- Uncomfortable, angry,
angrier, and madder.
That's why I started doing the, you know,
with her outbursts, I decided
to go ahead and do the video.
- And she kept going
even with you recording.
- Yes.
And she knew I was recording.
- So what prompted you to wanna post it?
Because it does put you at risk too.
The whole thing is so embarrassing.
Of course for her, because
she's doing all this stuff.
- I guess because as a
nurse and I have a platform,
that I thought that
bullying and body shaming
is an unacceptable behavior for children
and even more so for adults.
So I felt the need to actually show this
happening to me.
(audience applause)
- Good for you.
A lot of people would have just pretended
it never happened and
then it gets tolerated.
You travel a lot, have
you ever been publicly,
an attempt made to publicly
shame you like this?
- 15 years on the road and
this was truly a first.
I'm on the road almost every week
and this was a first.
- And you probably, you
must have at some point
been disbelieving this was even happening.
- I did, there was a delay.
But when somebody attacks
you in you're in public,
you can get up and walk away.
You're in a plane, there's
no place to walk to.
You're a confined space.
- In fact, maybe that's the reason,
but the airline ultimately kicked her off.
What was the reason they
gave for doing that?
- Well they were saying
that there were so many
people that were
complaining, besides myself.
When I got off the plane
there were people behind me,
when we got off the plane in Newark,
that told me that her behavior
after I stopped video taping
was she was still ranting back there.
So the airline had to
take her off the plane
for the safety of all of the passengers.
- So we reached out to the
airline, it was United Airlines,
and here's what they had
to say about the incident.
United flight attendants
care about the safety
and wellbeing of all of our customers,
which is why they acted quickly to find
a different seat for
the disruptive customer.
When it became clear that
this passenger's behavior
was likely to be
problematic on this flight,
she was provided alternative
travel arrangements
first thing the next morning.
So, she spent the night
wherever you were coming from.
Looking back on that tape,
why do you think that woman was so angry?
- I don't think I'll ever
know why she behaved that way,
and why she thought that
was acceptable behavior.
- Well, your brave desire
to share that experience
resulted in a video that
attracted 600,000 views
within a few weeks.
If you could talk to that woman,
and there's a pretty good chance
she might be watching this broadcast,
what would you tell her?
- Um,
she needs to be healed.
She needs to look inside and determine
why she behaved that way.
What is hurting inside herself that makes
her think it's okay to hurt other people?
Hurt people hurt people.
- [Dr. Oz] Yes, hurt people hurt people.
- Hurt people.
And she needs to understand
why she did what she did.
I am on the path of forgiving her,
because as a woman of god that is my job,
to forgive, and move forward.
(audience applause)
This is a teachable moment,
which is why I agreed to come on,
because this is a teachable moment.
I would like to take a quick moment
just to apologize to the
United flight attendants,
because they did an amazing job,
but for my language that
I used in the video,
to tell them I'm sorry
for using that language
at them when I was referring
to the other woman.
- I don't think you have
to apologize for that.
God bless you.
(audience applause)
Coming up, where's the line
between fat shaming and concern?
What should you do if you feel like
your doctor is fat shaming you?
Stick around.
(upbeat music)
Shocking update on the house of horrors.
Why would parents torture
their own children?
Louise Turpin's sister reveals
their intimate prison conversations.
Any expression of remorse?
An Oz True Crime investigation.
That's coming up on Wednesday.
Promotional considerations provided by.
- [Announcer] Shop online at Chewy.com.
- With Chewy.com I know
I'm getting an amazing deal
on my pet's food.
- [Announcer] At Chewy.com
you'll always find
low prices on your favorite brands.
Plus, you get fast free shipping.
- I just found my dog's food for less
than what I buy it in the store.
- [Announcer] Start
saving today at Chewy.com.
- [Dr. Oz] When you're
passionate about something,
anything is possible.
- Wow.
- That's Ensure Max
Protein, with high protein
and one gram sugar.
- It's a sit up banana, bend at the waist.
- I'm trying.
- Keep it up, you'll get there.
- [Announcer] 30 grams of
protein and one gram of sugar.
Ensure Max Protein.
- I got some good news for you.
You can win yourself
$5,000 a week for life.
My friends from Publishers Clearing House
can make it happen.
Win five grand a week,
week after week, for life.
August 30th it could be yours.
Enter now at PCH.com.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Arm and
Hammer plus oxi clean
with odor blasters detergent.
It eliminates tough odors
and blasts away the oof,
for a clean that will leave you in.
- Ahh.
- [Announcer] At a fraction of the cost.
In packs and liquid.
Arm and Hammer, more power to you.
- [Announcer] If you have
post menopausal osteoporosis
and a high risk for fracture,
now might not be the
best time to ask yourself
are my bones strong?
Life's full of make or break moments.
That's why it's so important to help
reduce your risk of fracture with Prolia.
Only Prolia is proven to help strengthen
and protect bones from fracture
with one shot every six months.
- [Announcer] Do not
take Prolia if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take Xgeva.
Serious allergic reaction
like low blood pressure,
trouble breathing, throat tightness,
face, lip or tongue swelling, rash,
itching or hives, have happened.
Tell your doctor about dental problems,
as severe jaw bone problems may happen,
or new or unusual pain in
your hip, groin or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone
fractures have occurred.
Speak to your doctor
before stopping Prolia,
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia can cause serious side effects,
like low blood calcium,
serious infections,
which could need hospitalization.
Skin problems and severe
bone, joint or muscle pain.
- [Announcer] Are you ready?
Ask your doctor how Prolia can
help strengthen your bones.
- With so many nourishing shades,
a color change is easy.
Nutrisse has 77, from our darkest blacks
to our lightest blondes.
It nourishes while it colors.
Plus avocado, olive and shea.
Change a little, or a lot.
Nutrisse, nourished hair, better color.
By Garnier, naturally.
- Unfortunately I was fat
shamed a few years ago.
I went to the doctor after a car accident
and he was supposed to
do some work on my back.
And while I was there he
told me that I, at the time,
I was 100 pound, almost 100
pounds heavier than I am now.
And he told me I should just go ahead
and have bariatric surgery done
because I was never gonna be able to lose
the weight naturally
and I was just gonna be
back in a few years asking for his help.
- I was gaining weight like crazy,
and I would go to my doctors for help
and all they ever said
was to work out harder,
eat better.
They said that I had fat genes,
they said I would always
have a weight problem,
they disregarded all of my other symptoms
and said I was crazy.
And this went on for about eight years,
and I finally did my own research
and discovered I had a brain tumor,
and that was causing
all of my weight gain.
And a year ago I had brain surgery,
I had the tumor removed,
since then I've lost 40 pounds.
(audience applause)
- We're back with our
investigation into fat shaming.
Could you be fat shamed
by your own doctor?
Where's the line between
concern about weight
and fat shaming?
Dr. Jennifer Corton joins us now,
we are hearing more and more stories
of patients they were fat
shamed by their doctor.
Why is their an increase?
- Well first of all,
this, it breaks my heart.
This absolutely breaks my
heart as a family doctor
to think of, to hear, and
I'll be honest with you,
you know, we're doctors,
I'm not entirely surprised,
and I don't actually think this is new.
I think we're hearing about it more now
because people are
willing to talk about it,
we're willing to record it,
we're willing to have conversations.
And things like social
media has really opened up
the platform to really share our stories
and compare experiences.
- So give us some advice,
give the average person
watching some advice as a physician.
How do you know if you're doctors just,
you know, doing his best,
or crossing the line--
- Yeah, into the shaming.
- Into the shaming area.
- Yeah you know this is what I always say,
I say trust your gut.
If it doesn't feel right,
if you don't feel right,
if you feel shamed or humiliated
or criticized or
embarrassed, you know what,
believe yourself, believe
exactly how you feel.
And a doctor wanting to do the right thing
does not excuse making a
patient feel any of those ways.
That's never okay.
And I say as a doctor,
and we're both doctors,
but I'll say, if you have a doctor that
makes you feel that way
or you're not comfortable,
I'm giving you permission
right now to find a new one.
- Let's give you some numbers on this.
Studies have found, hallelujah,
that overweight woman
are less likely than average
to get preventative care
like pelvic exams and
breast exams and mammograms.
There's no excuse for this.
But people treat overweight
people differently.
What is the right way for a physician
to address a patient's
weight do you think?
- Well I think there are a few things,
and first of all, as physicians,
we've gotta be talking about this.
These are discriminatory
practices, it's wrong,
we have to talk about it
and be very cognizant of it.
But as physicians, we need
to talk with our patients.
That's not talk at but talk to.
We need to ask our patients questions.
What's your journey?
How do you feel about your weight?
Tell me what you've bee
doing, what you've tried,
what your story is.
Asking questions is key.
And something that we've also talked about
is this idea of never
dismissing a patient's symptoms
just because of their weight.
We shouldn't dismiss patient's symptoms
because of anything, anything.
We should always be
doing our due diligence.
So this idea of saying
oh it's your weight,
just offhand, never okay in my opinion.
And the last thing is,
and this is something
a little bit different, you know,
I think in the doctor's
office, I'm a family doctor,
and do I take someone's blood pressure
out in a public space?
Or do I take their pulse
or their temperature?
No, never.
But sometimes in doctors offices people
are weighed in public
places, either in the hallway
or in waiting rooms or things like that.
And my thing is all of
this should be private.
This is our personal,
protected information.
It's no one else's business.
So there are things as
doctors that we can do better
to make this a more comfortable
and appropriate situation.
- Yeah you gotta feel
comfortable insisting that,
for example, you're weighed in private,
'cause I don't want you
not going to a doctor
'cause you're worried about it.
Weight's uncomfortable, I know.
That's true for a lot of us.
But it's a necessary topic.
So make sure you're
talking about the doctor,
not at but with, folks
as you care about it.
I wanna bring in Norma, the
nurse who we met earlier,
who was on the plane
and being bullied for...
Come on up, Norma.
(audience applause)
Norma, what's the best way, do you think,
a patient should be able
to address their doctor,
if they're worried about weight issues?
- Letting the doctor
know this is new to me,
this is an unusual feeling.
I've been feeling like this
for two weeks or two months,
putting a timeframe to it.
And if the doctor's still
not listening to you,
change doctors.
Always get a second opinion.
(audience applause)
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
- As always, we'll be right back.
(upbeat music)
I love getting to talk with you on my show
every single day.
But when the cameras stop rolling,
the conversation is not over.
I still have a lot that
I wanna talk about.
So download the Dr. Oz
podcast on Apple Podcasts,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
- I would get muscle
cramps several times a week
for decades.
Using Theraworx Relief,
the cramps are gone.
- [Announcer] Get Theraworx Relief today,
in stores everywhere.
- [Female] Starting a business means
I have to be well rested
every night of the month.
- [Announcer] Always overnight pads have
up to a two times larger back,
for up to 10 hours of protection.
It catches leaks so you can catch Zs.
- [Female] Because my morning
starts before morning starts.
- [Announcer] Always.
- [Announcer] This has potassium.
The same amount as this.
It's a post workout snack
you don't have to peal.
V8, the V is for vegetables.
Drink some.
- [Announcer] L'Oreal Paris introduces
rouge natural sunset matte lip stain.
Eight new warm shades.
Less texture, more colors, more Paris.
All day matte bare lip sensation.
Rouge natural sunset, by L'Oreal Paris.
- [Female] We're worth it.
- [Announcer] What might
seem like a small cough
can be a big bad problem
for your grandchildren.
Babies too young to be
vaccinated against whooping cough
are the most at risk for severe illness.
Help prevent this, talk to
your doctor or pharmacist today
about getting vaccinated
against whooping cough.
- Set your eyes on my latest game changer,
a world famous Bob-O-Pedic
queen mattress for only 299.
With all the quality and comfort
of its more expensive cousins,
it's really a little gem of a mattress,
so that's what we called
it, the Bob-O-Pedic gem.
- [Group] At Bob's Discount.
- Lifeguards not properly
trained or doing their jobs.
Pool areas that aren't
properly gated or up to code.
We trust that the pools
our families use to swim
are safe and secure.
But when a management or lifeguard company
fails to comply with
pool safety regulations,
tragedy can occur.
I'm attorney David Haynes
of The Cochran Firm.
If your loved one drowned due
to someone else's negligence,
call The Cochran Firm.
We'll help you get the
justice you deserve.
- [Announcer] Looking for that great job
but lack the experience?
- Not again.
- [Announcer] Let CET
help you get the training
you need for the job you want.
There are no semesters or quarters here.
You can start almost anytime.
Go from learning to earning.
CET is approved to train veterans,
offers financial aid and
job placement assistance.
Lots of programs to choose from.
Enroll today, start tomorrow.
Call CET and change your life.
- Get Bob's discount on furniture,
on lamps, on chairs, on mattresses.
On rugs too.
- [Group] Get Bob's Discount.
- [Announcer] Only at
Bob's Discount Furniture.
(audience applause)
(upbeat music)
- It's a big day!
I'm excited to announce the launch
of my all new Oz Guide.
They're new quarterly
single topic mini zines,
little magazines, cute little things,
that will tackle some of
your biggest health problems.
Our very first issue will
be on the news stands
and at supermarket checkout
counters later this month.
It's an Oz approved plan featuring
the healthiest fats
around, which are MUFAs.
'Cause you know, MUFAs are
monounsaturated fatty acids.
They're plant based fats so the
easiest way to remember them
is to look for healthy fats
that aren't from animal sources,
such as avocados.
Come bouncing down.
Or, you know what also
counts, nuts and seeds.
They can really fill you up.
(audience applause)
And one of my favorites, olives.
Black and green.
So there was a study done through
the American Diabetic Association,
that found that a diet rich in MUFAs
works to actually reduce belly fat.
It's a big deal.
But you don't wanna want...
We don't really want these
foods getting boring.
All right, that's the problem.
I know, I know, you're thinking that.
So I've been hearing reports
of nuts and seeds fatigue.
Shy away from this problem.
And then there's avocado apathy.
Nobody wants that.
Making headlines.
And then of course olive monotony.
One of the worst problems to run into.
So I have challenged
three Bite Club members
to come up with new MUFA-licious recipes,
in my first ever MUFA awards.
This is a very serious competition.
(upbeat music)
We have spared no expense as you can tell.
I hope you're impressed by that.
The MUFA awards, the
inaugural launch here,
the dishes were judged
by a team of tasters
who are harsh people, tend to
be sour and dour in nature.
So I'll present their reports to you.
Prior to the show they
tasted all these foods.
The winner will take home
our coveted golden avocado.
(upbeat music)
So I'm excited to hear
what they have made.
Jenny came up with a new
way to use nuts and seeds.
What did you make?
- So I made a burger.
I combined macadamia nuts,
almonds, cashews and pecans
with a lot of seeds.
Pumpkin seeds, hemp seeds, sesame seeds,
and quinoa, mushrooms, olives.
And there you go.
- You know it could have
been dry but it's not.
Very fulfilling.
Tastes meaty without the meat.
And rich in MUFAs as you described.
Nicely done.
- [Jenny] Thank you.
- All right, next up.
(audience applause)
Roberta came up with a next
level way to use avocados.
What did you do?
You have a sweet tooth don't you?
- I do.
Secret agent chocolate pudding.
- Very clever, diabolical.
- You know why?
- [Dr. Oz] Why?
- [Roberta] 'Cause our
avocado is the secret agent.
- It's a good name.
- Now this goes great with wine.
Sorry, I just had to
throw the wine in there.
- If you'd brought the wine it could have
influenced the judges.
- Right, probably.
So decadent, so delicious.
You wouldn't even know
there's avocados in there.
- It's very thick, and
it does fill your mouth,
and it's very chocolatey.
Nice combo.
And this is a very strong
competitor tonight.
But yours was too.
But, before we judge, thank
you very much, Roberta.
- You're welcome.
- We have Paula.
(audience applause)
Paula what do you have here?
You have an olive looking item here.
- So we have tahini filled hummus,
and these are actually
gluten free crackers
that are made from all those seeds
that just feel from the sky over there.
You love green olives.
- I do.
- Delicious.
And a lot of people eat...
Who eats hummus?
Everyone eats hummus, right?
- I love hummus.
- So I lightened the
hummus up a little bit
by adding some cauliflowers so it lowers--
- You did?
- Yeah, it lowers the calorie count.
You can't tell the difference.
- No.
- And then also this is a daikon radish.
This is a carrot, 46 calories.
10 calories.
If you need a vehicle to get
the hummus in your mouth,
try a daikon.
- Gimme that daikon.
I like this idea.
You put a lot of garlic in this,
I'm very proud of you.
- I did.
It's delicious isn't it?
So flat belly hummus.
- Speaks to my heart.
- All of these you will lose weight with
if you eat them the right way.
(audience applause)
But, I have the unfortunate
and difficult task
of revealing the winner.
Are we ready for this?
No hard feelings.
All right.
So I have deliberated with the judges,
and the first ever MUFA award,
and the person taking home
the golden avocado today is,
Paula!
- Oh my god.
- Oh my goodness.
Paula wins!
(audience applause)
(upbeat music)
- You like me, you really like me.
- I like all three of you actually.
Although you won this
and that was fantastic,
I gotta say, don't worry,
because we're gonna be
publishing both of your
recipes in the book,
the mini book zine.
So I'm very proud of you.
The OZ Guide to a flat belly,
it's available on news stands
and at supermarket checkout
counters later this month.
Check it out, share it with your friends,
and remember everybody, today
the change is happening,
our journey is just beginning.
I'll see you next time.
(audience applause)
It's really good.
(Sony jingle)
- Are you looking for a hassle free,
simple way to sell your home as is?
We buy houses directly.
There's no middle men, no commissions.
Give us a call today.
House Buyers of America.
Real estate made real easy.
- After my car accident, I
didn't know that a lawyer
would help deal with all my medical bills.
- I didn't know I could also get money
for pain and suffering.
- We do know.
Call 1-800-LAWYERS or
visit YouHaveALawyer.com.
If you have a phone, you have a lawyer.
- Keep it down there, I have a system.
- Keith used to be
great to road trip with,
but since he bought his house...
Are you going 45?
- Uh, yes.
55 is a suggestion.
- It's kind of like driving with his dad.
- What a sign, huh?
Terry, can you take a selfie of me?
- Take a selfie of you?
- Yeah.
Can you make it look like I'm holding it?
- He did show us how
to bundle home and auto
at progressive.com and
save a bunch of money.
- Oh a plaque.
He later navigated northward,
leaving the settlers...
- [Announcer] Progressive
can't protect you
from becoming your parents,
but we can protect your home and auto
when you bundle with us.
- [Announcer] At Pro
Plan we believe nutrition
is full of possibilities
to improve your pet's life.
We're redefining what nutrition can do,
because the possibility of a longer life
and a healthy life is the
great possibility of all.
Purina Pro Plan, nutrition that performs.
- Are you looking for a hassle free,
simple way to sell your home?