- We've got large hail--
- Rise and shine!
- [Both] Good morning,
Washington, from Crystal City!
- [Announcer] With ABC 7's Good
Morning Washington weekdays,
on your side, no matter where you are.
- [Announcer] The deadly blind
spot right under your nose,
tonight after the Oscars.
- [Announcer] This Week
with George Stephanopoulos
starts right now.
- [George] Countdown to Cohen.
- [Reporter] Do you have any concerns
about Michael Cohen's testimony?
- No, no.
- President Trump's former fixer
set to pull back the curtain
on his time with Trump
before three committees in Congress,
Cohen says he'll tell
the truth about Trump
after years of lies.
He's cooperating again with
prosecutors in New York.
Will this new testimony pose
a threat to President Trump,
even after Robert Mueller
completes his investigation?
That and more with House
Intelligence Chair Adam Schiff,
our legal experts, Dan
Abrams and Alan Dershowitz,
and Andrew McCabe, the FBI veteran
whose new tell-all is
drawing fire from Trump.
And--
- There's been no nuclear testing,
no missiles, no rockets.
- A second summit with
North Korea just days away,
but no signs yet that North Korea's
ready to give up its nuclear arsenal.
Will a second meeting with Kim Jong-un
bring real progress?
Insight and analysis from
our panel of experts,
including the ambassador who
negotiated with North Korea,
Bill Richardson.
Plus, Bernie is back.
- And our 2016 campaign began
the political revolution.
Now, it is time to
complete that revolution.
- His staying power shocked
the political world in 2016.
His national movement is
a fundraising juggernaut.
But can he stand out in
this cycle's wide-open race
for the White House?
Our powerhouse roundtable weighs in
on what's at stake in
2020, the issues in play,
and who's making headway
in these early rounds.
We'll break down the
politics, smoke out the spin.
The facts that matter this week.
- [Announcer] From ABC
News, it's This Week.
Here now, chief anchor
George Stephanopoulos.
- Good morning and welcome to This Week.
It is a big week ahead for the president
on two very different fronts.
Tomorrow he boards Air
Force One for Vietnam,
the site of the second
summit with North Korea's
Kim Jong-un, who's already
on his way to Hanoi.
You see him there in
his armored train that's
arriving in China yesterday.
But just as Trump tries to strike
a nuclear deal with Kim Jong-un,
Michael Cohen will take
the Washington spotlight.
Three days of hearings on Capitol Hill,
including blockbuster public testimony
in the House on Wednesday.
Cohen's lawyer says
he's prepared to reveal
damning details of his years
as Trump's attorney and fixer,
promising a chilling
portrait of the president.
It comes as Cohen continues
to cooperate with prosecutors,
offering leads into possible corruption
of the Trump inaugural,
and insurance irregularities
at the Trump organization.
And that investigation in
New York's Southern District
is just one of several probes poised
to challenge the president well beyond
the end of Robert Mueller's work.
We start with the man leading
one of those investigations,
the Chair of the House Intelligence
Committee, Adam Schiff.
Congressman Schiff, thank you
for joining us this morning.
- Thank you, George.
- Michael Cohen is going to
appear before your committee
behind closed doors on Thursday.
What do you hope to learn from him
that you don't already know?
- Well a great deal,
starting with why the false
statements before our committee
when he first appeared.
Did they go beyond what he told us
about Moscow Trump Tower
into other areas as well?
Who would have been aware
of the false testimony
that he was giving?
What other light can he shed
now that he's cooperating
on issues of obstruction
of justice or collusion?
What more can he tell us about the
Trump Tower New York meeting?
Or any other issues relevant
to our investigation.
We think he has a lot to offer.
- How about on the finances
of the Trump organization?
You've suggested that's the new front
in your committee's investigation.
- Well this is something,
George as you know,
I've been concerned
about for two years now.
We weren't really permitted
to explore it in great detail
when the Republicans were
running the committee,
but we know already, and Michael
Cohen is pivotal to this,
the peril of ignoring or
observing this red line
of the president's and
ignoring the financial issues,
what we have learned to date
about Moscow Trump Tower is chilling.
That is, as Donald Trump was
campaigning for president,
even when he became
the presumptive nominee
of the Republican Party,
and was telling the country
he had no business dealings with Russia,
he was privately,
through his organization,
seeking the Kremlin's help to make what
may have been the most
lucrative deal of his life,
even reportedly offering
an inducement to Putin
to make it happen, and at the same time,
talking about removing
sanctions on Russia,
something very important to Russians.
That is deeply compromising,
whether it's criminal or not,
it is deeply compromising
of our national security.
So those issues have to be probed,
and they include money laundering as well.
- That gets to a question about
the Mueller investigation.
If it turns out, as the
president has said so many times,
he did not collude with the Russians
to interfere in the election,
but in fact he was pursuing this
Trump Tower at the same time.
If that's not criminal, does Mueller have
a responsibility to report it or no?
- He does have a
responsibility to report it,
and in fact, if you take the position,
and I think it's a flawed one,
but if you take the position that
the president cannot be indicted,
and the only remedy for improper, illegal,
or other conduct is impeachment,
then you cannot withhold that
information from Congress
or essentially the president has immunity.
So that cannot be allowed to be the case.
Bob, or Bill Barr has
committed in his testimony
to making as much of the
report public as he can,
and the regulations allow
him to make it all public.
We're going to insist
on it becoming public,
and more than that, George,
we're going to insist
on the underlying
evidence because there is
certain evidence that
is only in the hands of
The Department of Justice that
we can't get any other way.
There were searches
conducted, for example,
of Roger Stone and Paul Manafort.
There's no other way
to get the information
that was seized except
through the Department.
We can't tell the country
fully what happened without it.
- As you know, William Barr
may have quite a different view
of what those regulation
require than you do.
They could allow him to
release the entire report,
but under Justice Department regulations,
officials have said that if you decline
to prosecute someone, then
the underlying evidence
should not be released.
- But George, the Department
has violated that policy
repeatedly and extendedly
to a great extent
over the last two years, and in fact,
I've had this conversation
with Rod Rosenstein
and others on down at
the Justice Department
as they turned over
thousands and thousands
of pages of discovery in the
Clinton email investigation
and there was no indictment
in that investigation.
This was a new precedent
they were setting,
and they were gonna have
to live by this precedent,
whether it was a Congress
controlled by the Democrats
or Republicans, so they're
gonna have to abide by that,
and I think also,
quite separate and apart from
the precedent already set,
is the intense public need to know here,
which I think overrides
any other considerations.
- You say the Justice
Department is gonna have to live
by that precedent, but what if they don't?
What if they simply
say no, we're not gonna
release the underlying evidence.
What options do you have?
- Well, we will obviously
subpoena the report,
we will bring Bob Mueller in
to testify before Congress,
we will take it to court if necessary.
And in the end, I think
the Department understands,
they're going to have to make this public.
I think Barr will ultimately
understand that as well.
Barr comes into this job
with two strikes against him.
He applied for the job by demonstrating
a bias against the Mueller investigation.
Indeed that's part of
the reason he was hired.
He's also not been willing to commit to
following the advice of ethics lawyers.
Indeed that was part of
the reason he was hired.
If he were to try to
withhold, to try to bury
any part of this report,
that will be his legacy,
and it will be a tarnished legacy.
So I think there will be immense pressure,
not only on the Department
but on the Attorney General
to be forthcoming.
- You're talking about public pressure?
Are you prepared to take
the Administration to court?
- Absolutely.
We are gonna get to the bottom of this.
We are gonna share this
information with the public,
and if the president is
serious about all of his
claims of exoneration, then he should
welcome the publication of this report.
- The president has said no
collusion many times as I said.
You said many months
ago that you've already
developed evidence of collusion.
We haven't seen that from Robert Mueller.
Do you have any evidence at all
that the president colluded?
- George, there's ample
evidence of collusion
of the campaign and it's very
much in the public record.
And it's everything from
what we have seen recently
about Paul Manafort
meeting with someone linked
to Russian intelligence
and sharing polling data.
And not top line data, not
this is why we think Trump
is gonna win data, but raw
data, complicated data.
We've seen evidence of Roger Stone
in communication with WikiLeaks.
We've seen the president's
son having a secret meeting
at Trump Tower that was
presented to him as part of
the Russian government's effort
to help the Trump campaign.
His acceptance of that help
is interesting, getting that.
All of this is evidence of collusion,
and there's much, much more.
Whether that will amount
to a criminal conspiracy
that can be proved beyond
a reasonable doubt,
we will have to wait for
Bob Mueller to tell us,
but to not see what is
plainly in front of us,
means you basically don't
wanna see the evidence
of collusion because it is quite abundant.
- Congressman Schiff, thank
you for your time this morning.
- [Schiff] Thanks George.
- Let's bring in our legal panel,
our Chief Legal Analyst, Dan Abrams,
also Harvard Law School
Professor Emeritus,
Alan Dershowitz, author of
The Case Against the Democratic
House Impeaching Trump,
and Dan, let me begin with you.
Let's pick up with what
I was talking about
with Congressman Schiff right there.
He says that Bill Barr is gonna be
under tremendous pressure to release
whatever Mueller has reported publicly.
It's not clear that Barr agrees with that.
- That's right.
Barr has made it very
clear that he's going to
release as much as he can, but
he has put caveats on that.
The question's gonna be, for example,
how much information in there potentially
could be a national security threat?
And I think you need to separate out
the difference between the report itself
and the underlying information.
'Cause you heard Congressman Schiff there
talk about some of the
underlying information.
That's gonna be harder to get.
- Even though it was all released in
the Clinton investigation?
- Correct.
Well look, you have to
remember that the current
Special Counsel law was a response
to the Clinton investigation,
meaning there were concerns
about how much-
- [George] The Bill Clinton investigation,
you're talking about the
Hillary investigation.
- Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I was talking about
the Bill, you're right.
In response to the Bill
Clinton investigation,
this was a response to that law.
On the Hillary Clinton investigation,
look, I don't think
there's a direct comparison
between the Hillary Clinton investigation
and the Special Counsel investigation.
I do think that there is a much stronger
argument to say that a
Special Counsel investigation
ought to be made public, even
if there is no prosecution.
That the decision making process for them,
that the report should be made public,
even if, and typically in
the Department of Justice,
you wouldn't release
information related to
an investigation that was not prosecuted.
- What's your response to that Alan?
- Well I think that's exactly the issue.
Democrats were appropriately furious,
I was among them, when Comey,
after saying that he was not gonna indict
Hillary Clinton then went
on to give his own opinion
as to her wrong-doing.
And the question is, is there
a difference between Comey,
who did wrong, everybody
now acknowledges that,
and a Special Counsel who has
had a broader mandate to investigate.
Look, let's be realistic.
In the end, everything's gonna come out.
There are no secrets.
In the end, it's all gonna come out.
And in the end, as I've said from day one,
it would have been so much better
if we had a non-partisan,
independent commission
like they have in England and in Israel,
like we had after 9/11,
getting to the whole truth
in a non-partisan way.
The American public's not gonna trust
a Democratic controlled House
- Let me stop you on that.
- They're not going to trust
the Republican controlled Senate.
- I'll take your point on the Congress,
but Robert Mueller was
about as non-partisan
a figure as you could
have found, isn't he?
- That's the point, no
that's the point now I think.
My point is that if his
information is not released
to the public, and it
then goes to Congress
to conduct the investigation,
I think there'll be
a question of credibility.
Look I think, and I've said from day one,
that President Trump's
greatest vulnerability
lies not with the Mueller report,
but with the Southern
District of New York,
and with the New York
Attorney General's office,
and with other prosecutorial arms that
can look into conduct unrelated
to collusion to Russia,
but conduct that preceded his presidency,
and I think that's where the problems
can come up in the future.
This may be just the beginning.
The Mueller report may be just a road map
given to Congress and
given to other prosecutors
that will continue these investigations
until the end of President
Trump's first term.
- I wanna pick up on that with Dan.
It does appear that we might be having
something of a Mueller
strategy in plain sight.
Every indictment he has
lays out in great detail
what he thought happened.
Meantime, things that
he thinks may be a bit
beyond his scope, he siphons
off to other prosecutors.
- Right, and I think
Alan's right that that
poses an enormous danger
to him as these other
offices because you can't just say
oh, well the Southern District
of New York is out to get me,
the Eastern District of
New York is out to get me,
and Virginia's out to get me, et cetera.
That's a tough argument to make.
But when you look at some
of the documents that have
been filed, for example
in the Manafort case,
and you talk about the
road map, you have to
ask the question in the big picture,
why so much still redacted, right?
Why are they still not allowing the public
to see so much related to
the Russia investigation?
Why isn't Michael Cohen being allowed to
testify in public about
the Russia investigation?
- He's only going to be talking
about other investigations.
- Right, about ten other
topics not related to Russians.
You have to ask yourself,
if there's nothing else
that's gonna come out, why
are they redacting so much?
- Alan, that was something curious.
800 pages from Robert Mueller yesterday
in the Manafort sentencing memo,
yet nothing about the underlying things
that he may have been lying about.
His meetings with various Russians,
and they say the redactions
were for ongoing investigations
and uncharged individuals.
That does suggest more to come.
- Oh absolutely, I have
no doubt about that.
I think these redactions are a clue
to what may be hinted at.
Look also, I think we
are seeing now an effort
to tamp down expectations from
the Mueller report itself.
I think we're being told
don't expect smoking guns,
don't expect dynamite in the report.
The report is gonna be the beginning of
some other investigations
coming down the line.
So I think there's a combination.
Don't expect too much from
the Mueller report itself,
but the Mueller report may
lead to greater investigations
by a variety of other institutions.
So this, the Mueller
report is not gonna mark
the end of the investigation.
I think that's the message we're hearing.
- Dan, so much of the report
and the Mueller report
is unfounded because Robert
Mueller isn't talking.
But there has been some rather aggressive
backgrounding going on suggesting
that the Mueller report
will be an anti-climax.
- Yeah, I mean, look, and the
expectation game is critical
when it comes to public perception.
But whether it's a summary, whether it's
a detailed accounting, don't forget,
we already have a lot of information.
I'm not talking just about
what Congressman Schiff
was talking about.
I'm talking about the
indictments that currently exist.
When people wanna know what happened
leading up to the 2016 election,
you have to start by
reading the indictments.
You have to start by
reading the indictments
of the Russians.
And then ask yourself,
okay, was anyone else
connected to them?
And that's what they're trying
to piece together still.
That's why when you
have Papadopoulos lying,
Flynn lying about Russia,
you've got Manafort lying, et cetera,
you have to ask yourself why are all these
people not telling the
truth about, and the answer
may simply be look, I wanted to
distance myself from it.
I didn't wanna get in trouble
in connection with this thing.
But there are still critical
questions that are unanswered.
There's a ton of redacted material,
and I think we're gonna
to see some answers.
- [George] And we're still
waiting for Robert Mueller--
- Let's remember, though--
- [George] Go ahead.
- Let's remember that indictments are
different than convictions.
A lot of this is indictments.
Remember, too, we're gonna see
a rebuttal report from the Trump team.
So I think the American
public should withhold
final judgment until
they see both reports,
the Mueller report and the
response by the Trump team.
- Well this will be the first
time in the history of America
where a defendant or someone
who's accused of something
gets to write a response report
to what an indictment is.
Every criminal defendant in America
would love to be able to
write their own report
about what they say happened,
but that's not the way the system works.
- But you're contradicting yourself.
- How?
- Because this is not just a yes or no.
You're saying that the Special Counsel
have special obligations
to release everything,
and if they have a special
obligation to release everything,
then there's an obligation
to allow a response.
- You can allow, that's fine.
- That's precisely the point.
- Let them respond.
- If it was just yes or no,
then you wouldn't need a response,
but if you get a long, long narrative,
then fairness requires a response.
- That's fine, let 'em respond.
- And simultaneous release of both.
- Whoa, simultaneous release of both, too?
So now basically--
- Right.
- Right, look.
That's just, that's ridiculous.
The idea that you have
to allow the other side
in something like this,
the opportunity to file
a long report in response to a prosecutor.
- You don't have to do that if
you just limit yourself to
indictment or not indictment.
If you go beyond it and
you start telling a story,
the other side of the narrative
has to be produced as well.
That's required by
fairness and due process.
- Bill Clinton would have loved that.
- Not in the regulations.
Okay, thank you both very much.
- [Alan] Well he should have gotten it.
- When we come back, his new book
is drawing fire from President Trump,
former FBI Deputy Director
Andrew McCabe up next.
And later the powerhouse
round table takes on 2020.
We'll be right back.
- [Announcer] This Week
with George Stephanopoulos
sponsored by Pacific Life
protecting generations
of families for more than 150 years.
That's the power of Pacific.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] When you retire,
will you act or feel different?
Or will you just be you,
without the constraints
of a full time job?
You can grow your retirement savings
with Pacific Life and create the future
that's most meaningful to you.
Which means you can retire
without retiring from life.
Having the flexibility
to retire on your terms.
That's the power of Pacific.
Ask your financial professional
about Pacific Life today.
- [Narrator] Family taco
night is a heartburn night
you can plan for, but
surprise pizza at the office
means heartburn you didn't expect.
Zantac works when you need it.
It relieves or prevents heartburn
in as little as 30 minutes
and lasts up to 12 hours.
Zantac, eat your way, treat your way.
- [Narrator] 98% of us
don't get enough omega-3s,
which is why MegaRed Advanced 4 in 1
packs more omega-3 power
into one small soft gel.
It supports your heart,
brain, eyes, and joints.
MegaRed.
- [Narrator] Prestige creams
not living up to the hype?
One jar shatters the competition.
Olay Regenerist hydrates
skin better than creams
costing over 100, 200, and even $400.
Fact check this ad in Good Housekeeping.
Olay.
- For singing, definitely dry mouth
has been a problem for me.
I'm also on a lot of
medications that dry my mouth.
I just drank tons of water all the time,
it was never enough.
I wasn't sure I was going to be able
to continue singing.
I saw my dentist, he suggested Biotene.
It feels refreshing, my
mouth felt more lubricated.
I use Biotene rinse twice a day,
then I use the spray throughout the day.
It actually saved my career in a way.
Biotene really did make a difference.
- [Narrator] Welcome to Fowler, Indiana.
One of the windiest places in America.
And home to three BP Wind Farms.
In the off chance the wind
ever stops blowing here,
the lights can keep on shining
thanks to our natural gas, a smart partner
to renewable energy that's
always ready when needed.
Or not.
At BP, we see possibilities everywhere
to help the world keep advancing.
- [Narrator] The Investigation,
the new podcast from ABC News.
Listen free on Apple Podcasts.
- [Narrator] For the
250,000 service members
who transition out of the
U.S. Military every year,
one of the toughest parts is the search
for a job that takes advantage of
the skills you've gained while serving.
You can now search with
phrase jobs for veterans
directly on Google and then enter
your military occupational specialty code.
Google brings together job openings
from across the web that match the skills
you gained in your military role.
Just click to apply
and use your experience
to guide your future.
- Pain wants to stop you,
block you, like that's gonna happen.
IcyHot, Icy to dull, hot to relax.
Rise from pain.
IcyHot.
- [Narrator] No matter how much you clean,
does your house still smell stuffy?
That's because your home is
filled with soft surfaces
that trap odors and release
them back into the room.
Try Febreze Fabric Refresher.
Febreze finds odors trapped in
fabrics and cleans them away
as it dries.
Use Febreze every time you tidy up
to keep your whole house
smelling fresh air clean.
Fabric Refresher even works for clothes
you wanna wear another day.
Make Febreze part of your clean routine,
for whole home freshness.
- [Narrator] This is Charlie not coughing
because he took Delsym 12 Hour.
And this is Charlie still
not coughing while trying
his hardest not to wake Zeus.
Delsym 12 Hour, nothing lasts longer
for powerful cough relief.
- [Narrator] Lady Gaga and Bradley Cooper
perform together live on
the Oscars, ABC tonight.
- [Narrator] There are
parents, neighbors, loved ones
living with diseases
like cancer, epilepsy,
mental health conditions, and HIV.
Maybe you're one of them.
But new Medicare rules could
deny access to the latest
most effective therapies,
therapies that keep them healthy.
Are Medicare cuts that save less than 1%
worth the risk to millions of patients?
President Trump promised
to protect Medicare.
We need him to keep his word.
- Why now may be the best
time to book a cruise.
Tuesday on Good Morning Washington.
- I think Andrew McCabe has
made a fool out of himself
over the last couple of days,
and he really looks to me
like sort of a poor man's
J. Edgar Hoover.
He's a, I think he's a disaster,
and what he was trying to do was terrible,
and he was caught.
I'm very proud to say we caught him,
so we'll see what happens.
But he is a disgraced man.
- President Trump taking on
our next guest, Andrew McCabe.
His new book The Threat:
How the FBI Protects
America in the Age of Terror and Trump
takes us behind the scenes at the launch
of the Mueller investigation.
Welcome to This Week.
Poor man's J. Edgar Hoover?
- I don't even know what that means.
It's not the first time
that I've had to listen
to the president say bizarre
and untrue things about me.
So it's unfortunate that this is getting
a little bit routine, but I will say,
I don't think there's
anything sad or unfortunate
about speaking truth to
power and telling the story
that you lived and the
things you saw and heard
and the reasons behind
the decisions you made,
and that's what I'm trying
to do with the book.
- Another man who's got
a reputation for speaking
truth to power, Robert
Mueller, you worked for him
- [Andrew] I did.
- At the FBI.
Based on what you know,
and you heard our previous discussion,
what should we expect from Robert Mueller?
Kind of a narrow by the
book prosecutor reporting,
or someone who senses he has a broader
responsibility to the public?
- That's a great question, George.
I think first and foremost, what you can
expect from Robert Mueller
is an honest, independent
assessment of the work that they've done.
How much detail he chooses to go into
to convey to the Department of Justice
is a great question.
I hope they lean on the detailed side.
This is not a normal
investigation by any evaluation.
It's one that I think
the Department, Congress,
and the public have an enormous interest
in finding out just
exactly what they learned.
- And it's complicated in so many ways,
including the precedent
of the Hillary Clinton investigation.
The FBI released all that
information about her
as you heard Alan Dershowitz say,
James Comey criticized for that.
Was that the wrong
decision by James Comey?
- I absolutely agreed
with Director Comey's
approach at the time, and
since have had the benefit
of some reconsideration of
those things that we did.
I think I'm pretty clear
about it in the book,
I think that decision
was not well thought.
I think we underestimated
the kind of political
toxicity of the environment that we were
launching our conclusions into,
and I think we overestimated our ability
and Jim's ability to convince people
of the great work that we had done.
- It is now a precedent, and in releasing
the entire underlying case file
is now a precedent as well.
Is it one the FBI should
follow in this investigation?
- I'm not sure that Jim's
decision to announce it in July
is a precedent.
However, I think that
it is a very concerning
and now recent precedent,
the volume of information
that the FBI turned over
to Congress in the wake of,
after the investigation was concluded.
That is something that
concerned me greatly
at that time, and I thought,
you know this is a practice
that will be hard to step away from.
- You made the decision to
investigate the president,
the opening investigation
into to the president
has come under some criticism this week
including from Congressman
Mark Meadows who says
you made a stunning admission.
You wanna put up his tweet.
Right there where you said it was
because of suspicious behavior
by the president on
intercept source reporting
or other secret evidence.
Congressman Meadows says
that is an abuse of power.
- I'm not sure what
he's referring to there,
but I can tell you that the information
that was in our hands at the time,
much of which was publicly known,
caused us great concern.
- You say us, but this was
your decision, correct?
- This was the recommendation
from the investigative team
and it was ultimately
my decision to authorize
the opening of the case,
and I did that because,
at the time, the facts clearly indicated
that we had an articulable
basis to believe
that a crime may have been committed
and that a threat to national
security might exist.
We hadn't concluded that
either of those two things
had happened, but we were
certainly in the place
that we needed to investigate both sides.
- You'd make the same decision today?
- [Andrew] Absolutely.
- You're also planning
on filing a civil lawsuit
against President Trump.
What grounds do you have to sue,
and what do you hope to get from it?
- Well, I can't talk in great
detail about the lawsuit,
I'll certainly let the
pleadings speak for themselves.
It'll be an action against
the Department of Justice
primarily, and challenging the
circumstances of my firing.
It of course derives from
the Inspector General Report,
a report that I deeply disagree with,
a report that was the result of a process
that I don't think anyone
has ever seen before,
I certainly hadn't.
(clears throat) Excuse me.
- Do you think the president
inspired that process?
- There's no doubt in my
mind that the president's
clear desire impacted that process.
The president was
talking about removing me
from months before I ever interacted with
the Inspector General.
He made his desires perfectly
clear on his own Twitter feed.
The Inspector General
delivered that result.
- Andrew McCabe, thanks very much.
- [Andrew] Thank you, George.
- Roundtable's up next,
we'll be right back.
- [Narrator] All money
managers might seem the same,
but some give their clients
cookie cutter portfolios.
Fisher Investments tailors portfolios
to your goals and needs.
Some only call when they
have something to sell.
Fisher calls regularly,
so you stay informed.
And while some advisors are
happy to earn commissions
whether you do well or not,
Fisher Investments' fees are structured
so we do better when you do better.
Maybe that's why most of our clients
come from other money managers.
Fisher Investments, clearly
better money management.
- How's your cough?
- I'm good, I took this 12 Hour Mucinex
and sent it far away.
- Hey buddy, have you seen
a nice woman with a cough?
Whoa!
- [Narrator] Mucinex DM release fast
and lasts 12 hours, not four.
Send coughs far away, all day.
- [Narrator] Think only
specialty stores have what's new?
Olay has the hottest debut.
New Olay clay stick masks,
hydrating facial mists,
and brightening eye cream.
Only by Olay.
- [Narrator] Whether you
were born for more dance offs
more travels or more touchdowns,
get the immune support
that gives you more.
Airborne gummies have 50% more
Vitamin C than Emergen-C.
Plus, our crafted blend of
vitamins, minerals, and herbs.
Airborne.
- [Narrator] Okay, so
when the New York Times
calls you one of the eight news podcasts
worth listening to, well,
you just say thank you.
So go on, start smart with Start Here,
free on Apple Podcasts.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] The Russells
travel to a different
swim meet every Saturday, but now
(sighs)
it's Thursday.
Good thing they discovered Gain Flings,
the only detergent with concentrated Gain,
Oxi boost, and Febreze odor remover.
Mm-hmm, smelling is believing,
and Gain Flings can
hi-yah karate stink, too.
Try new improved Gain Flings.
- [Narrator] 98% of us
don't get enough omega-3s,
which is why MegaRed Advanced 4 in 1
packs more omega-3 power
into one small soft gel.
It supports your heart,
brain, eyes, and joints.
MegaRed.
(slow electronic music)
- [Woman] Ignition sequence start.
110, nine, guidance in the terminal.
Six, five, four, three, two, one
(engines roaring)
- Pain wants to stop you, block you.
Like that's gonna happen.
IcyHot, Icy to dull, hot to relax.
Rise from pain.
IcyHot.
- Do I use a toothpaste
that whitens my teeth
or one that's good for my teeth?
Now I don't have to choose.
- [Narrator] From Crest 3D White,
the Whitening Therapy collection,
now with charcoal or coconut oil.
It gently whitens, plus it
has a fortifying formula
to protect your enamel.
Crest, healthy beautiful smiles for life.
- [Narrator] This is Charlie not coughing
because he took Delsym 12 Hour.
And this is Charlie still not coughing
while trying his hardest not to wake Zeus.
Delsym 12 Hour, nothing lasts longer
for powerful cough relief.
- [Narrator] Ah, potluck.
These dishes will soon be yours to scrub,
and they're not even yours.
New and improved Dawn Ultra
lets you scrub 50% less
and get done faster.
A drop of Dawn and grease is gone.
♪ My heart is feelin' a little bit low ♪
- [Narrator] When heartburn hits,
fight back fast with Tums Smoothies.
It neutralizes acid at the source.
♪ Tum, tum tum tum ♪
- Smoothies.
Also available, Tums Sugar-Free.
- Roundtable standing
by and all week long,
you get the latest on politics
and breaking news alerts
on the ABC News app, we'll be right back.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] This simple banana
peel represents a bold idea.
A way to create energy
from household trash.
It not only saves about
80% in carbon emissions,
it helps reduce landfill waste.
That's why BP is partnering
with the California company
Fulcrum BioEnergy to turn
garbage into jet fuel.
Because we can't let any
good ideas go to waste.
At BP, we see possibilities everywhere
to help the world keep advancing.
- [Narrator] Whether you were
born for more dance-offs,
more travels or more touchdowns,
get the immune support
that gives you more.
Airborne gummies have 50% more Vitamin C
than Emergen-C plus our crafted blends
of vitamins, minerals, and herbs.
Airborne.
- [Narrator] Upgrade to new Tide PODS 2.0.
And get 50% more cleaning power
in the palm of your hand.
For a powerful clean in one step.
Number one stain and odor fighter,
number one trusted, it's got to be Tide.
- When I kept finding
myself smoking in my attic,
hiding when I was supposed to be quitting,
I thought, you should
try something that works,
you should try Nicorette.
- [Narrator] Nicorette Mini relieves
sudden cravings fast, any time, anywhere.
Nicorette Mini, you know why, we know how.
- [Narrator] Prestige creams
not living up to the hype?
One jar shatters the competition.
Olay Regenerist hydrates skin better than
creams costing over
100, 200, and even $400.
Fact check this ad in Good Housekeeping.
Olay.
- [Narrator] Family taco
night is a heartburn night
you can plan for, but
surprise pizza at the office
means heartburn you didn't expect.
Zantac works when you need it.
It relieves or prevents heartburn in
as little as 30 minutes
and lasts up to 12 hours.
Zantac, eat your way, treat your way.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] This is decision tech.
It's screening technology
that helps you find
a stock based on what's trending,
or an an investing goal.
It's real time insights and information
in your own customized view of the market.
It's smarter trading technology
for smarter trading decisions.
And it's only from Fidelity.
Open an account with no minimums today.
- How's your cough?
- I'm good, I took this 12 Hour Mucinex
and sent it far away.
- Hey buddy, have you seen
a nice woman with a cough?
Whoa!
- [Narrator] Mucinex DM releases fast
and lasts 12 hours, not four.
Send coughs far away all day.
- I wanna make sure that
in the years to come,
the same opportunities
that were there for me,
a kid that grew up in the
public school in Texas,
can be there for anybody.
- I'm in this fight
because I truly do believe
this is our moment.
- I believe it is time to
restore truth and justice,
how about that?
- You see every single
day that President Trump
is trying to undermine our Constitution.
- I am going to run for
president, that's right.
- What's gonna be different this time?
- We're gonna win.
- First vote's a year away,
but the campaign already in
full swing this February.
Let's talk about it on our Roundtable,
joined by Chris Christie
our ABC News contributor,
former Governor of New Jersey.
Also author of new book Let Me Finish.
Heidi Heitkamp, former Democratic
Senator from North Dakota.
Rachael Bade, the new
Congressional reporter
for the Washington Post, welcome to you.
Patrick Gaspard, president of
the Open Societies Foundation,
Political Affairs Director
in the Obama White House,
also former Ambassador to South Africa.
And Alex Castellanos,
Republican strategist,
also an ABC News contributor.
Patrick, let me begin with you
and the case of Bernie Sanders.
He says he's going to
win this time around,
lot of questions, 77 years
old, already targeted
by the president as a
Democratic Socialist,
but 24 hours into his announcement,
$6 million in contributions
from that fundraising base.
- $6 million in right away
and another $600,000 from people
who have pledged to give
him every single month.
It's like the Netflix model of fundraising
for a presidential campaign.
But he's going to have
an interesting challenge
this time around.
I worked on Howard
Dean's campaign in 2004.
- Against John Kerry.
- Against John Kerry
and everybody else in the world,
and early on in that
contest, there was a sense
that it was a battle
for the hearts and minds
of the Democratic party,
but at some point,
in Iowa and New Hampshire,
South Carolina early on,
Democrats decided we
don't want a revolution,
we just wanna beat George Bush,
and we've got to find
somebody the most electable.
I think that Bernie Sanders
is going to find this time,
people don't want a revolution,
they wanna beat Donald Trump.
- Heidi Heitkamp, it brings
up an interesting point.
Bernie Sanders, his
ideas have been adopted
by many other candidates,
many other Democrats,
but there is that concern that he's gonna
pull the party too far to the left.
- Well I think that a couple
things are gonna happen.
You're gonna see people get in
who are gonna broaden the
scope of Democratic ideas,
that are gonna be put on the forefront,
but to the point of the money.
Money doesn't matter as
much as what it used to,
in my opinion, and when you step back,
and you take a look at
kind of the record crowds
that everybody's enjoying in Iowa,
I mean people are coming out
because they wanna examine
each candidate and pick the candidate who,
in their mind, the highest priority
is who can beat this president.
- Money may not matter, but
the sign that you've got
this movement behind you could.
- It could, but I
disagree with the senator,
having gone through it a couple
years ago, money matters.
Because, what's going to happen is,
whoever emerges out of this will wind up
having a huge target on their back
when they start to do well,
and they have to have the money to answer.
If you don't have the money
to answer, you're gonna lose.
Because, I love all the characterization
of Iowa and New Hampshire
voters, especially early,
as being so discerning and they wanna come
and meet you in person.
They wanna meet everybody in person,
but they also watch what
comes in their mailbox
or what comes over the
TV, and guys like Alex
wouldn't have made the fortune he's made
over time if that didn't matter.
It does matter, the money will matter,
and Sanders will matter.
But it's a Republican dream that Sanders
could actually be the nominee.
- Can I just jump in real quick and say
it is increasingly, the difference between
Democrats on Capitol
Hill and these Democrats
jumping in to 2020 are
becoming increasingly glaring.
When you see all these
candidates supporting
Medicare for all, the Green
New Deal, free college,
all these ideas, getting
corporate money out of politics.
On Capitol Hill, Nancy
Pelosi is keeping her arms--
- But she's holding the line against some
of her new members as well there.
- Well they're introducing ideas,
but they're not gonna be
voted on on the floor.
And there's a reason for that,
and that's because most
Democrats on the Hill
are afraid of these ideas, and they think
they go too far and they're gonna--
- In a presidential campaign,
politics will just swamp
public policy over the course
of the next 18 months or so.
- [Rachael] They're going
to have to be careful--
- Capitol Hill will be taking a back seat
to what's happening in--
- It shows in the divide
in the party, though.
- President Trump loves
the idea of Bernie Sanders
front and center.
- Oh, he couldn't be that
lucky again could he?
Look, the president has
seen a Democratic party
going as crazy far left as Republicans
did far right under
Obama, and it's a gift.
Socialism didn't work for the Pilgrims.
The first two years, half of them died,
and now that's the
Democratic party agenda.
There are three Democratic
primaries to take on Trump,
and all of them are gonna,
there's the Establishment
primary with Biden
and Klobuchar--
- [Patrick] Can't get more Socialist
than the Quakers, right?
That was their model.
- You're going to have
the Progressive primary
which Sanders has the money and the lead.
Then you've got Kamala
Harris and Cory Booker
for the Obama Black primary.
Which one, I think Kamala
Harris is gonna succeed
in that one, you're
gonna see Bernie Sanders,
maybe Klobuchar--
- Alex.
- I would bet you right
now that Kamala Harris
can grow beyond, I think she's being,
she's a big enough candidate--
- I'd be careful there,
there's no such thing
as the Obama Black primary.
- Yes, I think there is.
- I think Kamala Harris
and Cory Booker are both
extraordinary candidates
who can appeal to a broad cross section.
- That's my point about Kamala Harris.
I agree with that, and I
think that's right now--
- You're all judging the
Democratic party ideas
by the people who are in now.
What happens when Michael Bennett gets in?
What happens when Sherrod Brown gets in?
What happens when you
see Bloomberg get in?
- What happens is they--
- You mention Joe Biden,
you think he's getting in?
- I do.
I think Joe will get in.
I think the Vice president
will feel a calling
will feel a necessity
to bring that gravitas
and I think that the minute he gets in,
he's going to be the
recognized front runner.
- [Rachael] And there's an
opening for that right now.
- Joe Biden is hot, he has name ID,
a lot of Democratic
voters are sitting there
because they don't know the alternative
but the soul of the
Democratic party is rabidly
anti-Trump and it has gone crazy left.
It belongs to Ocasio-Cortez,
not Joe Biden.
- The soul of the Democratic Party
- That is wishful Republican thinking.
- The soul of the Democratic
party, respectfully Alex,
there are folks who are sitting in Iowa,
New Hampshire, South Carolina,
California which is an
early state on Super Tuesday
this time who are worried
about the education
of their children, they're
concerned about health care.
- Which is why Elizabeth Warren--
- They're terribly concerned
about some of the corruption
we have in Washington, DC.
- Is for reparations.
- At the end of the day, here's the issue.
We're gonna dominate,
we're gonna move away
from politics of ideas
- Let's get to what's practical here.
Let's get to what's practical here.
And what campaigns come
down to are candidates.
Forget about all the
ideology and everything else,
it comes down to candidates.
- Who's gonna perform?
You've seen this, I've seen this,
I've lived it.
Who's going to get up there and perform?
Kamala Harria, you know
learned this in her first week,
when she's talking smoking
pot listening to Tupac,
when Tupac's albums hadn't come out
until six years after she
said she was in college.
You're shaking your head,
Patrick, but let me tell you.
She's probably told that
BS story in California
a thousand times and no
one ever called her on it.
When you run for president--
- But Governor--
- They call you on everything.
Who's going to perform
when the, there's only
two alternatives, George.
- We're going to judge them by whether
they tell the truth now?
(laughs)
that's a new standard for president!
- The Governor is saying
something terribly important.
- When the lights go on,
there's only two alternatives.
You either shine or you melt.
Those are the only two alternatives
for presidential candidates
and we're gonna see
who does what, and I
think it's way too early
to try to figure it out with these folks.
And when Joe Biden is
seen as the front runner,
which I think he is if he gets in,
this is a guy who's run twice
and hasn't exactly shined
both times he ran.
- Governor, you know a thing or two about
fanciful tales and that type of thing.
- [Chris] Aw, Patrick.
- At the end of the day,
the Governor is right
that this really is about performance.
When you showed that clip at
the very beginning, George,
every candidate with the
exception of Amy Klobuchar
started each sentence with I.
I believe, I feel, they understand
that at the end of the
day, it's whether or not
people can trust them and
their values and their story.
- Rachael, one of the things
we've been seeing is that,
since the government shut
down, the president's
actually had something of a
come back in recent weeks.
Approval ratings back up,
heading towards the mid-40,
not quite there yet, but this whole idea
of the emergency going to back
front and center on
Capitol Hill this week.
- No, exactly, I mean
the president thinks that
this is a good re-election,
something he can run on.
That it's gonna help him.
And, you know it shows that he's obviously
catering to his base,
and he's showing that he
is putting them front and center,
but it's interesting
because, in doing that,
he has sort of upended the
re-elections potentially
of other Senate Republicans.
There are 22 Senate Republicans.
- They don't want this vote.
- They don't!
and a lot of them were privately
telling the president
please don't do this.
Don't do this, this is
gonna create a terrible
precedent if we have a President
Bernie Sanders some day,
if he's gonna try to do
something with the Green New Deal
on his own, call it an
emergency, this a big problem.
And we can't have that.
But we're already seeing a lot of
those same Republicans who privately
were telling him don't do
this, come out and say that
basically they're not going
to push back against him.
- Still his Republican
party, and by the way,
if the election were held today
against the Democratic
party he's running against,
I think Donald Trump will win
by more than he won last time.
The Democratic Party is going crazy left.
The only thing that has changed,
neither party has changed by the way,
Republicans or Democrats
since Trump was elected,
except Trump is now not theory, he's fact.
And it's an impressive record--
- [Patrick} It's a fact
that the mid-term Elections
- Growth and security, excuse me--
- Were a creation of that fact.
- But see, that's the thing--
- You can't forget that happened.
- No, that's important, but actually--
- Where suburban white men in particular
have been fleeing from this president
- What you have to
understan, mid-terms are
a referendum on the incumbent.
Presidential years are
choices, and the Democrats
are offering a choice of going left,
Trump is saying--
- The Democratic choice is not yet--
- The economy is growing, I'm locking--
- The Democratic choice is not clarified,
that's why you have the
primary contests, Alex.
- Let me just say Trump's choice is clear.
Growth and locking the
doors at night and security.
The Democrat's response has
not been about either of those.
It's only been about the mommy bear party,
caregiving and nourishing.
It's like a 1950s sitcom and in that case,
the teddy bear party usually
beats the mommy bear party.
- So health care, child care-
- I'm not advocating,
I'm just telling you,
Trump has got a very strong hand going.
- If you think the economy in a year
is gonna look like the
economy today, you're wrong.
And the tax refund issue
is real, I know this.
You can say well their taxes were reduced.
People count on that refund,
and now they feel they got shortchanged.
They look at economic
and business investment
that never materialized.
They look at a package,
the signature piece,
economic piece for this president--
- Hoping for bad news is not
a great political strategy.
- No, no, and I'm not hoping for bad news.
But I think bad news is
predictable in this cycle.
I mean I'm not the only
person saying this.
I think look at one of the leading--
- [Alex] It is if you're a socialist.
- Indicators in the
economy is agriculture.
We have record bankruptcies
in the farming industry.
- Alex is counting on that
socialism label sticking,
but Chris, I wanna bring
up a different point
inside the Republican party.
It does seem to be
Trump's Republican party.
Right now, we have Bill Weld say that
he's going to run against him.
Larry Hogan, Governor of Maryland,
had this to say this week.
- I was just sworn in a
month ago for my second term.
I've got a lot of work
to do here in Maryland.
I would say I'm being
approached from a lot of
different people, and I guess
the best way to put it is,
I haven't thrown them out of my office.
- How real is this idea of a significant
challenge to the president?
- Not, not real.
Listen, there's probably
nobody in American politics
who knows Larry Hogan better than I do
because I was the guy who I in 2014
went in there when no one
thought Maryland was winnable
and I invested $2 million in Larry Hogan,
and we got him over the finish line.
Larry Hogan won both times,
only the second Republican
ever to be re-elected
Governor of Maryland in
the history of the state
because he's a smart politician.
And a smart politician is not,
based on this set of facts,
gonna challenge Donald Trump in a primary.
Because the guy's got 80%
approval ratings among Republicans.
And so I think what Larry's
doing is he's got some issues
he cares about, he's gonna
use this as a platform
to speak out about those issues, to try to
bring the party a little bit
back towards where he is,
but the idea that Larry Hogan,
and Bill Weld's not serious,
no one takes Bill Weld seriously,
Larry Hogan would be
serious, but he's not.
My view is, he's not gonna do it.
- It seems like it would
be, it's political suicide
to do that right now.
I mean this is Donald Trump's
party still, two years later.
Look no further again to the
National Emergency Declaration.
- [Patrick] Provided
there isn't a revelation
that comes out of these investigatons--
- Then by the way, Larry
Hogan would be with
a whole group of people who
were running if that happened.
- Republicans were out
speaking against this
Emergency Declaration for weeks.
He totally ignored them and
now they're backing off.
This is Trump's party and
running against him is foolish.
- The question is what
does happen with these
farther on investigations
throughout Mueller?
We still haven't Robert
Mueller's report either, Senator.
Do you sense any concern among your former
colleagues on Capitol Hill
that if Robert Mueller
finishes his job and hands it off to them
that they're going to be
wary of going too far?
- I hope so, I think they are.
I think they realize that
one of the worst things
that can happen, in my
opinion, is impeachment.
I think that you have
to win at the ballot box
in order to have a real
future for this country.
- [George] Does that
mean no investigating?
- No, it doesn't mean no investigating,
but it does mean that what do you do
with that investigation?
All of that information is
critical, it's important.
The public needs to know.
I said 20% of the public, guess what?
They believe whatever the president says.
The next 20% will look at this and say
yeah, he doesn't always
tell the truth but so what?
I mean so you've got 40% who
aren't really gonna ever care.
You're looking at the 20% that
you hope you could persuade.
- That's what the polls say now.
The past is prologue, senator.
I remember the polling a year before
President Nixon resigned
said that 50% of Americans
thought that too much media attention was
being paid to Watergate.
The polling on the day that he resigned
said a quarter of Americans
still supported Richard Nixon.
So I just, I think that you--
- [George] You're full speed ahead?
- I think Democrats in
Congress are absolutely
going to continue these investigations.
There's more than enough
fodder when you consider
that every institution that
Donald Trump has touched
has come into being questioned from
his cabinet picks like his
current Labor Secretary
to his foundation that he had to shutter.
- Here's the thing, though, it that
there better be some there there.
If they're going to decide
to go down that road,
- Mountains of there.
- Patrick, this is a
different context now.
Because when you're
getting into a presidential
election cycle, people
are going to see it as not
being necessarily legitimate,
but being political.
Even more political when you're gonna have
all these candidates
that they're not going
to be able to control themselves.
- How does that affect
your former colleagues
in the Southern District
right now who seem to have
the most serious investigation
in the Trump investigation?
- Not a lick, not a bit.
They don't care.
That's why we were, when I
was US Attorney of New Jersey,
every other U.S. Attorney
used to refer to them
as the Sovereign District of New York.
They believe they are a
sovereign power unto themselves
in the Southern District.
They'll listen to no one.
They barely listen to
the Attorney General.
So they're going to do whatever
they think they need to do,
and that's what I've
been saying as you know,
for 10 months here, the
Southern District of New York
investigation is monumentally
more perilous to the president
that Bob Mueller ever was or ever will be.
They have two tour guides, George,
and no restriction on where they can go.
- That is the last word today.
Thank you all very much.
Up next, our experts
break down what to expect
from President Trump's
second nuclear summit
with North Korea's Kim Jong-un.
We'll be right back.
(suspenseful music)
- As of today, we are all
officially working together.
- As a team.
- [Both] Led by me.
- She is just trying to push your buttons.
♪ Warrior ♪
- How about a warning next time?
- Okay, we're here.
- I am going to win you over.
My charm is like a virus.
Before you know it, boom, you're infected.
- So you're going to give me a virus?
- [Narrator] Whiskey Cavalier,
special sneak preview
after the Oscars, series
premier Wednesday on ABC.
- [Narrator] Hey Mercedes,
take me to the Red Carpet.
- [Narrator] The all new
Mercedes Benz A Class,
with MBUX, featuring natural
language recognition.
Join us to watch the stars arrive.
Mercedes Benz, the best or nothing.
- [Narrator] This is what she sees.
This is what's really there.
Is it possible to avoid hitting
something you can't see?
Seven on your side
investigates the dangers
of front over crashes
tonight after the Oscars
and Monday on ABC 7 News at six.
- They have to get rid of
all their nuclear weapons.
- They've got to get rid
of, yeah, I think they will.
I really believe that he will.
I've gotten to know him over--
- Did he tell you that?
- A short period of time,
yeah sure it's de-nuking.
I mean, he's de-nuking the whole place,
and he's gonna start very quickly.
I think he's gonna start now.
I'd just like to see
ultimately denuclearization
of North Korea, and I think
we will see that ultimately.
I have no pressing time schedule.
- President Trump resetting
expectations there
for his second nuclear
summit with North Korea,
that's set for Thursday in Vietnam.
Let's talk about the risk
and the possible rewards
of that meeting with our panel of experts,
Tom Bossert, former Trump
Homeland Security Adviser,
ABC News contributor.
Jung Pak, Brookings Institution
Korea Studies Chair,
former CIA Analyst.
And Bill Richardson, former
U.S. Ambassador to the U.N.
Who has negotiated with North Korea.
Ambassador Richardson,
let me begin with you.
You saw the president resetting
the expectations there.
He also has a tweet out
this morning that ends
with denuclearization
with a question mark,
questioning whether that's gonna happen.
Can you have a successful
summit without a clear
commitment by the North Koreans and actual
concrete action to denuclearize?
- I don't believe it would
be a successful summit
unless you had some kind of
commitment on North Korea's
part on denuclearization,
dismantling, inspections,
missiles, nuclear detonations.
It seems a president
deflating expectations,
and that's a concern.
The concern 'cause I
think what should come out
of this summit is a
framework for negotiations.
My worry, George, is
that this negotiation,
this summit may be a dud, that
instead of concrete progress
on what is important,
denuclearization, it's now shifting
from denuclearization,
arms control, to peace,
to important steps, return of
our servicemen, the remains.
Maybe a liaison office,
maybe some kind of continued
North South cooperation, which is good.
I think the president deserves
credit for lowering tensions
in the region, but in terms
of concrete accomplishments,
I don't think this summit's
gonna produce that.
- Dud is, I guess, one possibility.
There's also been some concern
expressed by the president's
advisors that he gives away something that
he shouldn't give away too soon,
say a formal peace declaration,
a formal declaration
end to the Korean War.
- I think Bill is right.
I think there's been a profound
shift in talking about peace
and normalization with North Korea
rather than the nuclear issues.
And I think that's really problematic
because the whole point of a
summit between the two leaders,
is to get dismantlement
and to get North Korea
to completely abandon
it's nuclear weapons.
I think having a peace
declaration and normalization
is fine for tension reduction,
but we really have to wonder about how
that affects North Korea's
actions down the line.
- Should there be, Tom Bossert,
should there be a summit
now given the fact that
the president's own
National Security Advisor,
John Bolton says that North
Korea hasn't followed through
on the commitments they
made at the first summit.
- There's been
back-pedaling and dishonesty
from the last summit
which was a significant
watershed moment 'til today.
At this point, the only
reason to have that summit
is for President Trump to go in
and give a clear-eyed reminder.
It will be a dud if he comes out and tries
to varnish this as a success without
any real actionable activity.
Any kind of freeze or reversible gesture,
superficial gesture on the
part of the North Koreans,
is gonna be a little bit
of a slap in the face,
but if the president then
comes out and buys it,
whether it's because of
domestic political pressure
or some other instinct to post a win,
he's going to lose the
international coalition
that he's put together and
the strength he goes in with.
- The president had
another tweet this morning,
Jung Pak, that the president put out,
he says that North Korea can
be an economic powerhouse
under Kim Jong-un if they just give up
their nuclear weapons.
Almost trying to incentivize
him to come further along.
At this point, he does seem to be banking
on the idea that his personal relationship
with Kim Jong-un is somehow
gonna yield benefits.
- Yeah, I think President
Trump is making the mistake
of mirror imaging, so the
president is from New York City.
He's a business man and
a real estate mogul,
and he's speaking in terms
of as if Kim is another
business man, but Kim is a dictator
of a highly authoritarian regime,
who needs his nuclear
weapons for legitimacy
and his own survival.
And so yes, North Korea is in the middle
of a very strategic environment
among the second, third, and 11th largest
economies in the world.
But North Korea also sees its location
and its economic deprivation
relative to the other
countries as a threat
to it's survival.
- So how do we make progress short of
North Korea getting rid
of it's nuclear weapons?
The testing moratorium, we've seen
testing moratoriums in the past.
What kind of concrete action
could we see from North Korea
that would really signify
real progress that can be built on?
- I think Jung is right and so is Tom.
My view is that, what
is concrete progress?
One, I've called this a potential dud,
but we've got to continue
talking the relationship--
- There's no harm.
- No.
The relationship of the
two leaders, that's good.
However, the president should
listen to his advisors,
and his advisors have been,
I think, very specific.
What I fear we're gonna lose, one,
a detailing of all the weapons inventory
that North Korea has.
I think we've kind of given up on that.
Secondly, that we simply say okay,
you dismantle the Yongbyon
reactor, another missile site,
that they've already done several times.
That's a danger, and if
that's the only arms control
initiative that they push.
I think lastly, my worry,
George, is that we're gonna trade
something what the North Koreans
really want which is a peace treaty
in exchange for some limited
arms control measures.
I think what needs to happen
is dismantle some weapons.
They're not going to
dismantle all of them.
Freeze intercontinental ballistic missiles
that affect Japan and South Korea.
Find ways that these are concrete steps.
Timelines, verification, a
framework for negotiations.
If it's just a bunch of hand shakes,
and you're a good guy, we'll meet again,
it's gonna be a dud.
- Is there a win win here?
- Yeah, but it's not going to
happen out of this meeting.
So what happened in the
last meeting took us back
from the brink of war, but the president,
two presidents agreed
to two mutually inconsistent
future objectives.
One was normalization
between the North and South,
and the other was
denuclearization of the North.
Right now, president Moon in the South
is suggesting that he give some incentives
in terms of money or
reductions in sanctions
or opening up industrial
complexes to the North
to induce them into further talks,
to re-normalize their relationships.
That would fundamentally
undermine everything
that President Trump is trying to do
with respect to denuclearizing.
If you don't force him, to Jung's point,
the North will not get
rid of their weapons.
So the win win here has
to be for the president
to carry the international
good will to this meeting
because he's not representing
the United States
and come out of this with some serious,
if not threatening additional sanctions.
- That is the last word for
today, thank you all very much.
That is all for us today.
Thanks for sharing part
of your Sunday with us.
Check out World News Tonight,
and I'll see you tomorrow on GMA.
(intense energetic music)
- [Narrator] We all need someone
who will pull no punches
and give it to us straight.
No bull, no spin.
Now imagine getting your news like that.
Just give it to me straight.
ABC News, straightforward.
- Empire actor Jussie Smollett
took advantage of the pain and anger
of racism to promote his career.
- [Narrator] GMA exclusive,
Chicago's top cop.
His first interview in the stunning
Jussie Smollett investigation.
What will he say now?
Tomorrow on Good Morning America.
- Show me The Crown.
- [Narrator] Look at you.
When you talk, your TV listens.
That's cool.
Downloading 24 tunes in one second.
Boo-yah.
Locking your doors with your phone?
Oh yeah.
Jim and Melissa, you are cool.
- [Man] Cool.
- Hi Carol.
- [Man] Let's go!
- [Narrator] Get Contour
TV, 100 meg internet,
and now Homelife Automation
for $89.99 a month.
Free HD camera included.
- [Narrator] Traffic Watch 7 is our way
of keeping you ahead of traffic,
so you can commute better, save time,
save headaches, and save money.
It's team traffic, on your
side to help find which turn.
- And a good alternative to 95 right now.
- [Narrator] Which side
road, which highway to take.
On the maps with Julie Wright.
- Mobile Track, the first on the scene.
- [Narrator] On the roads
with Mobile Track 7,
and in your car with
new Traffic Watch 7 app.
Traffic Watch 7, on your side.
No matter where you go.
- [Announcer] The deadly blind
spot right under your nose.
Sunday after the Oscars.
(upbeat music)