- The Poconos, Ashley.
- Let's visit some small towns
with great food, shops, and
of course gorgeous views.
- She does have all the answers.
- [Narrator] Watch for Pocono
Mountains Magazine on FOX 5
or go to PoconoMountainsMagazine.com.
- [Narrator] What comes with a dollar
soft drink from McDonald's?
(upbeat music)
$1 any size soft drink.
Joy included.
(electronic music)
(upbeat music)
- Welcome to TMZ Live, Harvey Levin here.
- Charles here.
- Bill Cosby is giving lectures
behind bars on parenting,
on drug abuse, and on getting a job.
And he's drawing huge crowds.
- He is essentially, and extremely popular
motivational speaker in the prison
where he is serving his term.
- Now, this may sound crazy to you,
because Bill Cosby,
at the end of this trial
where he was convicted,
you know of drugging Andrea
Constand and assaulting her,
You would think that
people aren't listening
to Bill Cosby anymore, they are.
They are behind bars.
- And it's happening
multiple times a week.
This is three, four times a week,
and up to 100 prisoners will
elect to come to these things,
it's not a required or mandatory thing.
These guys are coming
to listen to him talk.
- And you know, Brandon and
I were talking about this,
that you think about,
what is it that's different between them
and people on the outside?
And you know, people in prison,
especially if they've
been there a long time,
they are locked into the Cosby show.
- Right.
- And didn't necessarily connect to--
- But they know why he's there.
- They do indeed, but it
doesn't seem to matter
the way it matters on the outside.
- Brad, do we know if,
is he like acknowledging:
Look I've made mistakes,
is that part of his--
- He has maintained his innocence
through this whole thing,
and actually to the Cosby show part,
his rep told us whenever
he's there to visit Bill,
a lot of the prisoners still refer to him
as their dad or their father figure,
and that's I think,
also part of why they're
listening to him here.
- And you know there are people, you know,
who commit certain crimes in prison,
or commit certain crimes in the outside,
and when they come in they're
looked on with disfavor.
It is the opposite with Bill Cosby.
- [Commentator] Yeah, I mean, it's dicey.
I mean--
- Yeah.
- In this particular case,
it's dicey for a lot
of reasons, number one:
The crimes of Bill Cosby,
a big deal I've heard,
heinous and deplorable, right?
At the same time, there are still people
that look at him with a certain affinity,
and up until those
crimes were made public,
he was an insanely successful person.
So if you're going to,
in a vacuum, if you're
gonna listen to somebody
on how to become successful,
or things that you need
to do to reclaim success,
or start some of your own,
he wouldn't be a bad guy to listen to
besides all of the other
stuff you don't wanna hear
that's coming out of his mouth.
So, if you're inside, you
might look at it differently.
- So Brad, in terms of the substance
of what he's talking about with parenting,
I think he's talking about re-bonding.
- Yeah, because a lot of
the guys that he speaks to
are going to be out on parole soon.
So they've lost time with their kids
so it's about re-bonding with
your family and your children
when you get out.
And it's also about how
to interview for jobs,
and go find work right away
so that you're provided
opportunities that don't
land you back behind bars.
- [Harvey] It's interesting that--
- It's not that what he's saying,
what he's saying, I'm sure there's,
clearly there's value in it.
- Yeah.
- There's value in it,
and a lot of these men
he's speaking to in there
can learn something from it
and from him.
It's just weird that it's coming from him
after what he was convicted of--
- But I guess the question--
- I guess the question,
when you're on the inside
everybody has made--
- If not, a rue.
Everyone's made a mistake.
- Everyone there has made
a mistake, clearly.
- Right.
- At the same time, you know, listen,
if you're incarcerated,
whatever it is that
you're incarcerated for,
you would hope that someone would spend
their time inside, incarcerated,
to try to do something positive.
Like anything, you know,
toothpaste you can
squeeze out of the tube.
I guess it's just a weird
thing coming from Bill Cosby
at this point with the ideas that we have
in our head about him right now.
- I just think it would
be less distasteful
if he were acknowledging some wrongdoing
while teaching these lessons.
And because he isn't, it's
like if he's not contrite,
then for people on the outside,
it's just difficult to
hear him being a leader.
That's how I feel, that's what I think.
That's why this story seems
weird to people I think.
- Hi, my name is Markeish Johnson,
and I am from Milwaukee, Wisconsin.
And speaking about Bill Cosby,
I think it is very rare
for us on the outside
to hear of what Bill Cosby is doing,
however I think it is very
beneficial to the inmates
that are coming out on
parole, due to the fact that
you know, they're gonna
come back on the outside,
they're going to re-bond
with their families
and rebuild and try to
fit into that life again.
So, I think it is a good
idea for Bill to be doing
something of that,
while he's incarcerated,
but he also needs to admit
to his wrongdoings as well.
(upbeat music)
- Mayor Pete Buttigieg is an incredibly,
we know he's very accomplished--
- [Harvey] Smart.
- [Charles] Incredibly
smart guy, Road Scholar.
- [Harvey] He speaks multiple languages
by the way.
- Speaks multiple languages,
which was on display in New York City.
- So he's walking down the street,
and this dude comes up to him,
and the guy is from Malta.
And he is actually, he is the president.
What's funny enough
it's a president-hopeful
meets a president.
He's the president of a Maltese club
in a store in New York.
So, (laughs) the guy starts
talking to Buttigieg,
and we're not gonna tell
you the whole thing--
- Here's a little bit.
- In Maltese, watch this.
- All right, my people, Maltese.
(speaking in foreign language)
- [Charles] So you want to be President.
It's not the weather.
- [Harvey] No, I don't know.
- [Charles] No, they're having a talk.
- [Harvey] I know, but what
are they talking about?
- [Charles] We know, because
we have Maltese spies.
- All right, so here's what I know,
that what the guy from Astoria is saying
is he's inviting Buttigieg--
- [Charles] This is a rough translation.
- Well yeah, I talked to somebody.
So he invited Buttigieg
to come speak at the
club that he runs in
Astoria, and then decided
to sweeten the pot by
saying that if you show up,
we're gonna give you,
help me out with the name
of this thing, the can, it's a dessert.
What's the name of it again?
- It is called, I don't know.
Oh here it is, pastizzi.
- Pastizzi.
- Which is a, it's kind of like a cannoli
with a soft crust on it.
I believe it's ricotta cheese inside.
But they ended up talking
- That doesn't sound
like a dessert.
- And it turns out
that Buttigieg was asking this guy,
where he was from.
- Where his family was from
in Malta.
- And then Buttigieg said
that his grandparents
were in a nearby town,
and they live next door
to a guy named Anton
Buttigieg, not related to him.
- Not related, but they're the same--
- Became president of Malta.
So, Buttigieg is like Smith
in Malta.
- In Malta.
- Because there are a lot
of people named Buttigieg,
which I didn't know either,
so it's kind of interesting.
- Another thing
that we learned here,
first of all we should say
in addition to Maltese,
Mayor Pete also speaks
Italian, French, Norwegian,
Spanish.
- Spanish.
- [Commentator] He's read
books in those foreign
languages too, like he
doesn't just speak though,
like he really knows them.
- [Charles] And he also
speaks some Arabic, anyway.
- [Harvey] So, I was just interested--
- The other thing we learned is,
and we should say this
'cause I don't wanna make
the assumption that everyone knows
where Malta is, Malta is a small island
in the Mediterranean, and it's basically
between Africa and the
end of the Italian boot.
- Thank you for that.
- Some people think that it's
near Greece for some reason.
- It is near Greece.
- It's not near Greece.
- Well it is near Greece.
- It's near to Africa.
- It is near Greece.
- It's very near to Africa.
- I didn't say nearer,
I said near Greece.
- Tunisia, Tunisia,
that's where it is.
- It is near
Greece.
- Look on a map, folks.
- Look on a map
and you'll see.
- And you'll understand that--
- You will see that it's near Greece.
- And we're done.
- Hi, this is Glorashtee,
I'm calling from Chesapeake, Virginia.
Mayor Pete is going to sneak up on us all.
He has the unique ability
to bond and blend,
and connect genuinely
with just about everyone.
And he's only like what, 19 (laughs).
- You got some millennial shade?
- It might a bit. (laughs)
It might a bit.
- Look, I think what's
really fascinating about him,
we gotta move on, is that
he is a true intellectual.
And, it's interesting that, you know,
how America receives that
- Receives that--
- I think they're gonna receive it well.
- Right, instead of--
- Because you also can relate to people.
- Right, what you're saying
is that there's always
the chance that some people
feel alienated from that,
that like you're--
- You know who'd change that?
- Who?
- James Holzhauer.
- Oh, there you go.
(Harvey laughing)
(upbeat music)
Let's get some dancing in.
Very real dancing.
Beyonce and Jay Z's little
girl's all grown up.
- Well she's seven.
- She's seven,
but that's old enough
to be the star of a dance recital.
Blue Ivy attends Debbie
Allen's Dance Academy,
here in the LA area.
I think it's in Inglewood, actually.
And she had a recital
and was doing her thing.
She actually also--
- [Harvey] She's good.
- [Charles] Yeah, she looks good.
Now she did this, but
there was another time
when she's performing to
one of Beyonce's songs,
"Before I Let Go", and--
- She's really good.
- Which has gotta be,
I don't know, is that weird for her?
Well I guess, my mom.
- No, it's not weird for her
because they probably play the song
all the time in the house.
She probably listens to the
radio, it's always on the radio.
And kids love that song,
everybody loves that song right now.
Like, there's a huge viral
"Before I Let Go" challenge
that I'm sure she does at home
in her mirror with her mom,
so it feels like at home,
and she's killing it, so.
- [Harvey] Do the other
kids think it's weird, then?
- [Commentator] No, they're kids.
They're like six years old.
- Why don't we just let
these babies dance.
- My niece loves this song.
(man laughs)
- Let these babies dance.
- But Beyonce redid this song
and brought it back for
- Hey, hey.
Uncle Van, Uncle Van.
- a whole other generation.
- Easy Uncle Van, okay.
- What you saying, man,
it's a bunch of kids.
Is it weird for 'em?
(Harvey and Charles laughing)
Let these babies dance, man.
- Let these babies dance.
(men laughing)
- [Charles] Fine, okay.
Dance babies, go ahead.
- God, can we take a break?
(men laughing)
Oh my god.
- Yes please, let's do this.
(upbeat music)
- [Kyler] It's something I've
dreamed of my whole life.
- [Announcer] Touchdown!
- [Nick] I love this game,
it's part of my family.
- [Quinnen] On the field, on the base deep
as a player in the country.
- [Announcer] The weather's heating up,
but TMZ's cooler than ever.
(people laughing)
TMZ, we love Hollywood,
we just have a funny way of showing it.
- [Announcer] Tonight at 7:30 on FOX 5.
- Selling your house?
We'll buy it as is, handle all repairs,
and there's never a fee.
Get to life's next step even
faster with peace of mind
and cash in your pocket.
♪ Express Homebuyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
- You've tried so many moisturizers
(water splashes)
But one blows them
all out of the water.
Hydro Boost with hyaluronic
acid to plump skin cells
so it bounces back.
Neutrogena, and try our hydrating makeup.
(mic tapping)
(clears throat)
- My Calvin sofa and loveseat only 699.
My Calvin sofa and loveseat
or two-piece sectional only 699.
or two-piece sectional
with throw pillows only 699.
My Calvin sofa and loveseat
or two-piece sectional
with throw pillows and your choice
of three colors only 699. (gasps)
My Calvin sofa and loveseat
or two-piece sectional
with throw pillows and
your choice of three colors
and Bob-O-Pedic seating
for extra comfort only 699
and only at Bob's Discount
Furniture. (sighs heavily)
My Calvin collection, it's
a lot, just not expensive.
- [Crowd] Get Bob's Discount.
- [Bob] Only at Bob's Discount Furniture.
(children chattering)
(relaxing music)
(beeps)
(jingling)
(children screaming)
(children laughing)
(water splashing)
(children chattering)
- [Narrator] Get the best steal on tickets
at KingsDominion.com.
Kings Dominion, it's amazing in here.
(upbeat music)
(camera shutter clicking)
♪ Body talk ♪
- The only thing that
I would do differently,
the only thing.
I should have called
Express Homebuyers sooner.
♪ Express Homebuyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
(crowd cheering)
- [Narrator] If you come at the Queen,
you best not mess.
(thunder clapping)
(upbeat music)
- Welcome back to TMZ Live.
If you're Halle Berry, and you come home
to your fabulous house, only to discover--
- [Harvey] It ain't your house no more.
- [Charles] It's not your house.
It's just--
- [Harvey] This is mind-boggling.
- [Charles] That's a good
word, mind boggling--
- So she literally, there's a guy
who tried to steal Halle Berry's house.
Steal her whole damn house.
- Yup, how in the world do you pull off
something like that?
- Well he figure out a way.
- Yes, police say this is how a guy named
Ronald Eugene Griffin (laughs)
tried to do it.
- [Commentator] This
is such a crazy story.
- [Charles] It's so, it's actually simple.
- [Harvey] It starts with a locksmith.
- So this guy firstly comes
back to the house in January
and tries to fiddle with the locks,
and the gardener comes, he goes,
"What are you doing here?"
And he takes off.
He comes back later, like a month later.
He comes back with a locksmith
and they start working
on the outside locks,
and they get one of the locks changed.
And someone from the house
who works there goes,
"Hey, what are you doing?"
He goes, "Oh, I'm the
new owner of the house,
"I have the deed here".
The person from the house says,
"Well I'm gonna call the cops."
Well this guy goes, "Well
I'm gonna call the cops too".
- [Harvey] Because I have the deed.
- Yeah, I mean this is so crazy.
- So the person who's lived,
this is one of Halle's
homes in the L.A. area,
it's not, apparently not her main home.
- [Harvey] But, but--
- [Charles] If there's a staff, again,
at that point right there, then to me
that's where an alarm should have gone off
that the staff, or whoever
was there at the house
might make a call to
Halle Berry or somebody--
- I think they did call
her, they called the police,
and then eventually this guy,
they investigated, this guy
ended up being arrested.
- So they started looking
at this guy.
But the guy actually forged the deed.
- [Commentator] Right, forged the deed,
and this is more common
than you believe now.
There's a whole division
that deals just with this.
People are doing this.
They'll steal a whole house,
they'll go and change the deed.
- And one of the problems with this
is if you think about it,
and this has been a big thing
in California and in
a lot of other states,
where elderly people especially,
they get taken advantage of,
and it's done in various ways where they,
you know, a roofer will come
and say, "Hey, you know what,
"sign this contract, and
we'll put a new roof on,"
and they end up foreclosing.
But this is way more bold but--
- Yeah, this is, I mean it's shocking
having to steal a whole house.
- But if somebody doesn't
have the staff to fight back,
like "Get out, it's my house now".
- Yeah, I mean if it's a
rental house or something,
you go there and they're like, "No."
And then you gotta go through the process
of evicting them, and
getting them out legally
and they could be there for a while.
- So remember, Halle Berry has had issues
with, you know, intruders in her home.
I don't know if you remember
but four or five years ago,
she literally came back to her house,
got in the kitchen, looked
out the glass window
in the kitchen and
there's a guy facing her
on her property staring at her
who's trying to get inside the house.
And it was somebody who
apparently had been persistent.
So she's had these problems before.
- Correct.
- But apparently the guy
didn't know it was Halle Berry's house.
- No, I mean this house was under a trust,
so he had no idea, it's just random luck
that it was Halle's, or unlucky for Halle.
- Bad luck, bad luck for him also.
- He got arrested.
- Hey, I'm Ariel Jones
from Atlanta, Georgia.
I think that it's just so weird
that you find another person in your home,
especially Halle Berry, and it's like
how he'd think that he
would get away with that.
- [Harvey] That's actually
a really good question.
- [Charles] Well that's
what I was gonna say,
like I can't imagine how he did,
but the fact that he
did this makes you think
that he probably did actually
pull this off at some point.
- This is such an important point.
My dad owned a liquor store,
and I don't remember what happened,
but we always used to say
that bank robbers don't
start robbing banks,
they start stealing
candy at liquor stores.
- Correct.
- And then they graduate up.
So to go to a really
nice house where you know
there are employees there.
- He probably pulled it off
with a smaller house.
- That's right.
- They're worth less.
- 100%.
And you're just wondering how
many times has this happened,
and are they getting, you
know, people who are struggling
out of their house and saying,
"Go, go, you're gone, it's my house now."
And they do it.
I mean it's crazy.
Okay, we're gonna move on.
(upbeat music)
- We got some video now of a huge brawl
that broke out,
I guess it's not a huge brawl,
it's only two people.
- It's a brawl.
- But man it was vicious.
On a New York City street
corner, this is in SoHo,
two women for various reasons,
according to witnesses,
just started going at it
until a Hollywood actor
named Peter Greene,
you know him from "Pulp Fiction",
you know him from "The Mask".
He plays--
- He's a pretty good actor.
- Yeah, he's played the
villain in a lot of things.
He played Zed in "Pulp Fiction".
But he happened to walk by
while everyone else was
watching what was going on--
- Jumped into action.
- He jumped in.
(women shouting)
(car horn honking)
(beeps)
- Stop fighting!
Just calm down, just calm down.
Hey, hey, no, stop fighting!
Stop hurting her!
Stop hurting her with the rag!
(beeps)
- Yo, stop hurting--
- Stop it, stop it!
Stop it!
(beeps)
Why can't you two stop it,
what's the matter with you?
You let 'em fight?
You're a grown man, what the (beeps).
No, tell you!
Stop the fighting between two women.
What's the matter with you?
- [Pedestrian] How come he didn't stop it.
- (beeps) Stop it.
(car horn honking)
(people chattering)
- [Charles] You could see at the end there
Peter was ticked off.
- Grief with Peter Greene.
- The people he was yelling
at are New York City
traffic agents who were
standing on the corner.
- And just watching it.
- And watching it happen,
so he was chastising them.
- Good for him.
- You can understand why he'd be mad.
I mean, isn't that their
job to keep the peace?
Why are they just standing
there watching two girls beat
the hell out of each other?
- Well, yeah, I mean, look,
they do work for NYPD,
they're not actual officers,
they're traffic agents,
but they do work for NYPD.
- [Harvey] There's a problem,
and you know it's interesting
'cause Peter, you know,
these bikes are not cheap.
And Peter just kind of
throw down his bike.
- Well no.
- [Harvey] Well yeah, I
mean it's pretty valiant
when he did it.
- [Commentator] All the
human trauma happening
and Harvey's not listening.
- Harvey's looking at how
expensive that bike is.
- I'm concerned
about that bike.
(men laughing)
- [Harvey] No, I'm just
saying it's a marker
of how he's stepped in, he
was such a good Samaritan.
I think it just adds to--
- [Commentator] Stop right there, Pete,
you don't wanna pick up a charge yourself.
- [Charles] Right. (laughing)
Good for him.
- It is good to step in.
But I don't know, Tim,
- Well you wanna
see the side of her face--
- The traffic people,
I don't know if they're like,
if that's part of their job description,
they give out tickets, right?
- It's probably not.
Yeah I know, but you know.
- I think if the fight had spilled over
into the crosswalk,
then it affects traffic,
then they would get involved.
I'm guessing, but I--
- [Commentator] Or they could
just be decent human beings.
- [Harvey] Well, yes.
- [Commentator] Wait,
hold on, hold on, hold on,
stop, stop, stop.
So a decent human being puts themselves--
- [Harvey] Yeah, at risk.
- [Commentator] At risk
to get in the middle
of somebody fighting?
- [Harvey] And someone's spitting, also.
I don't know about that man.
- [Commentator] Obviously,
y'all never really been
around that bit fighting.
You let them go 'til they tired.
- Yeah, there's a difference
between being a good Samaritan
and not being decent.
I mean, look, people don't
wanna get involved, it happens.
But, I mean, good for Peter Greene.
- Good for Peter Greene is
what we should be sayin'.
Don't shame everybody else,
Peter Greene did something heroic.
- I'm Victoria Brownlee from
Greensboro, North Carolina.
And I must say that
video was pretty amazing,
he did it just so effortlessly,
and then put everybody else in his place.
His status just went up
10 notches in my opinion.
- All right.
- Okay, and we're moving on.
(upbeat music)
- Okay, wanna hear about a cool cat?
- (laughs) A real cool cat
is gonna make a lot of money,
at least that is the plan.
You guys know Benjamin Button, right?
Not the movie character,
but more importantly
Taylor Swift's feline.
- Yes, her third cat,
her newest cat added to the
family earlier this year,
is now officially part of the gang,
because she has added
Benjamin to her trademark.
Now, last year she had,
how do you get Benjamin
Button as a trademark?
- She got a--
- Well it's Meredith,
Olivia and Benjamin Swift.
So that's the difference,
and now she's gonna--
- It's almost like
Benjamin Button is a nickname,
but his trademark name
- Oh, his government name
- is Swift.
- is Benjamin Swift.
- Yes.
- I got it.
(laughing)
- Yeah, so Taylor added Benjamin
to the trademark she had--
- [Harvey] Has she done
anything with the other cats
in terms of marketing anything?
- Yes she has, Meredith
and then the other one, Olivia,
have been like all over T-Shirts
and everything like that.
So she has already been
selling all that merch,
and now with him, I
mean it's just gonna be
even more cuter.
And she wants to do like
cellphone cases, luggage,
I mean there's so much
opportunity for this guy,
and you guys, with
grumpy cat passing away,
the cat community
is heartbroken.
- There's a hole
in the market, yeah.
- There is absolutely
a spot for a new cat to
come in and take over.
- You know that Benjamin's not actually
gonna make any money, right?
Like the money all goes
to Taylor.
- No, you're kidding me!
- Well, I've just seen, we
wanted to let Charlie know,
because she sounded pretty excited about
opportunities for Benjamin.
- You guys, maybe it's not
about the money for him,
maybe he just wants the fame.
- See, that's why I needed Florida.
- Yeah, he's a clot chaser,
he's a cat chaser.
Taking a break.
(upbeat music)
- [Woman] Feel this clean and fresh
without a shower.
New Vagisil Sensitive
Scents Dry Wash is here.
For instant freshness on the go.
With no white residue,
just spritz and go, girl.
Sensitive?
Meet Vagisil Sensitive Scents.
- What we achieve for
patients is life-changing.
- You get your smile
back, your confidence back
in just one day.
- A new smile at a price you can afford.
- With the dignity and
respect you deserve.
- Don't wait another day.
Nothing is more life-changing
than a healthy, confident smile.
- [Narrator] Let affordable
dentures and implants
create your new smile.
Schedule your free consultation.
Call 1-800-DENTURE, or visit
affordabledentures.com.
(calming music)
- Ready to go when you are.
- Wow, you look nice.
Getting around isn't as
easy as it used to be.
That's why we called Bath Fitter.
They removed our old tub,
and installed a beautiful
new spacious shower.
Now, getting in and out is a breeze.
And, we have peace of
mind with seamless walls
that provide a water-tight fit.
Plus, their lifetime guarantee.
Thanks to Bath Fitter,
life is so much easier
with a shower we love.
- [Narrator] Call today
for this month's offer.
- Duke's is far and away
my favorite mayonnaise,
and it has been for as
long as I can remember.
It tastes homemade, but it's
better than I could make.
- [Katie] For any potato
salad, you have to have mayo,
and we might as well start with the best.
- And it's Duke's.
- And it's Duke's. (laughing)
- Really good!
- The fact that they use real egg yolks,
and there's no added sugar,
you can actually taste them.
(crunching)
Oh yeah!
There's more Duke's on
there than there is Bologna.
(both laughing)
(relaxing music)
- I'm Andy Bederman of a law firm
of Greenberg & Bederman.
For over 30 years, my
law firm has been helping
personal injury victims
in the DC Metro area,
get the financial
compensation they deserve.
If you've been hurt in a car accident,
been the victim of medical malpractice,
or been denied social
security disability benefits,
please let us help you too.
Call us at 301.589.2200,
or visit us on the web at GBLawyers.com.
Greenberg & Bederman, call us feel better.
(upbeat music)
- Buy one, take one is back,
starting at just 12.99 at Olive Garden.
Join us for a new favorite today,
then bring one home for tomorrow on us.
Buy one, take one for a limited time.
Only at Olive Garden.
- [Narrator] TMZ's got
every freaking thing.
Big celebs, big stories, big events.
- [Woman] Teyana Taylor gave Iman Shumpert
a sexy lapdance at her concert.
- [Man] Oh, this is
good, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- He had sweats on, that's dangerous.
(people laughing)
- [Narrator] It's TMZ.
(upbeat music)
- Welcome back to TMZ Live.
Most of the faces are the same,
but man have their lives
changed dramatically.
Talking about the cast of "The Hills".
The reboot "The Hills:
New Beginnings" on MTV.
And yes, you will see a
lot of faces that you know,
A couple of faces that are new.
- [Harvey] They've had a decade to grow.
- Yeah.
- And change.
And what's interesting
is, everybody thought
Heidi and Spencer was only
for the cameras back then.
Remember, it was 2006 to 2010.
And there was a come
on, Heidi and Spencer,
they're together.
- Still together.
- They're married.
- Married, and yeah,
there's that little guy
who is on the show, which is interesting
because we know that having
kids on reality shows--
- Problematic.
- Can be problematic.
So joining us right now
to talk about all of that
is Spencer Pratt.
- [Harvey] Hey Spencer, sir.
- [Charles] Welcome back to TMZ Live,
how you doin', man?
- Oh my god, whoa.
Can I see your guys' faces, I can't see
my big head like that.
- Where are you?
That's beautiful.
- That looks awesome.
- That is Crested Butte mountains.
- Ah, Colorado!
- This is where I grew up.
We're visiting her family, oh my god.
- [Charles] Montana?
- [Harvey] No, Colorado.
- Colorado.
- Crested Butte, Colorado.
I didn't know if it was Colorado.
God it's beautiful there.
- Isn't it though, yeah.
- [Harvey] Holy smokes.
- It's unreal I was
wondering if you wanted
to enjoy the view.
- Well we appreciate that.
So listen man, because it's been a decade,
and there were no, when
you guys were partying
in Hollywood back then,
nobody was bringing baby strollers.
- Yeah!
- [Charles] Or car seats, so
how's this gonna work out?
- That was a big drama thing for my wife,
because she is an attachment parent.
So the first part of The Hill,
she doesn't really go out,
and she's having serious,
I would say emotional
breakdowns just leaving our son.
'Cause for the first year
she never left Gunner
for longer than a minute,
which is amazing, but is
was also very challenging,
so thankfully for "The
Hills", she gets to a point
where she can go out and be a regular mom,
that is fun, and has a drink.
But, that was very challenging initially.
- Okay, I got a question because that,
I didn't know this.
So, this sounds like a,
was she preventing you
from parenting because she
was doing it all the time?
That's what I'm hearing.
- No, no I was there,
I could leave the house, she
was way more like extreme.
Obviously, Gunner didn't
come out of my body,
so I imagine that connection's
a little bit more intense
than, you know, my connection.
- That's a fair assessment
probably, yeah (laughing).
- So what about, you've
heard about Rob Kardashian
and Blac Chyna arguing over
whether their kid can go
on a reality show, and whatnot.
Do you have any like
trepidations about Gunner--
- Yeah, did you guys talk about it?
- Sometimes it doesn't end well.
- What was the conversation
like before you made
the decision about having him on?
- All due respect to Rob and Blac Chyna,
but we've been together 12 years,
so our relationship's a little stronger
(Charles laughs)
than those two, which you know
I hope I--
- That's not shade,
those are facts.
- Yeah, yeah, so I think
that's the difference.
We're very aware of what reality TV does,
and if Gunner initially had
not enjoyed the process,
and you know, didn't like people,
we wouldn't have done it.
But he would cry when they would leave.
He would be trying to hold the boom mics,
and it was like fun, almost
like an adventure for him, so.
You know, he's more like an Asahd,
he's like DJ Khaled's son,
they were born for it.
- Okay Spencer, we're gonna play a game.
This is total fantasy land.
Pretend I'm 19 years old,
and I'm trying to figure out
- Okay, what is going on here?
- what I'm gonna watch tonight,
and I'm thinking, wait a minute,
these folks are married
now, they got a kid.
I wanna see people
partying and doing whatnot,
what they did in the OG, so--
- Wooh, I got you Mister
19-year-old Harvey Levin.
(men laughing)
Okay, let me tell you about
Brandon Thomas Lee,
the son of Tommy Lee, the
son of Pamela Anderson.
He just turned 22.
He is the King of Hollywood.
The guy has more dates
than anybody I've ever seen in my life.
He's got breaking hearts,
he's a freaking supermodel,
walking runways.
Real talk, he's cooler
than any of us ever were
when we were on "The
Hills", he's the next level.
So he's bringing that
19-year-old interest.
And then if you're one
of these older people--
(Harvey laughing)
- More seasoned,
more seasoned.
- Yeah, or better, but I will say
that one thing about being a parent is
when you do get to go out,
like I was allowed out
two nights a week.
(Harvey and Charles laugh)
I party harder than
any 21-year-old could ever party,
'cause I'm like, "I'm
out of the house, ha!"
So I would say I drank and partied harder
than ever before on this season.
I was actually, like my
goal was to out-party
any of these other reality shows.
And I think I did it, I
was going to every scene
with two bottles of Don Julio, so.
- Oh gosh!
- Excellent answers, Spencer.
- All right.
- Excellent answer, yeah.
- Thank you, thank you.
- I think 19-year-old
Harvey is in.
- By the way, there
was once a 19-year-old.
- I know.
- Brandon is a superstar.
He cut out his own show on
MTV, just called "Brandon",
so he's our ringer.
- [Harvey] He is--
- You gotta send in the ringer.
- Okay, Spencer
congratulations, it's amazing.
You guys endured the show,
endured, it's amazing.
- Thank you Harvey, I
will tell this now finally
feels real to talk to you again,
I feel like I'm in a time machine.
- I know, this is crazy.
- It's like old times,
like old times.
- Spencer, congrats and send
the same regards to Heidi.
- [Charles] And Gunner.
- And Gunner.
- All right, love you guys.
- [Harvey] And Gunner.
- Thank you to all the
TMZ Live commenters,
you guys are some of the funniest people.
When I'm bored I go and read TMZ comments
(Harvey and Charles laughing)
You guys are professionals,
so got off the--
- Oh god.
Okay, Spencer, we'll see you.
God it's beautiful there, holy smokes.
- That's god's country right there.
- Okay, taking a break.
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- Start the car!
Start the car!
- [Narrator] The IKEA Summer Sale.
- Woo!
- [Narrator] Save up
to 50% off select items
in store, only June 26th to July 7th.
IKEA.
(relaxing music)
- Can you actually love
wearing powerful sunscreen?
(waves crashing)
Yes.
- [Narrator] Neutrogena Ultra Sheer.
No other sunscreen works
better or feels so good.
Clinically proven Helioplex
provides unbeatable
UVA/UVB protection to help prevent
early skin aging and skin cancer.
All with a clean light feel.
For unbeatable protection.
- It's the one, the best for your skin.
- [Narrator] Ultra Sheer, Neutrogena.
- See what's possible.
- [Narrator] It's gonna
be a summer scorcher,
and what better way to beat
this heat, than on our Caribbean Cruise.
That's right, with a
purchase of any new car
at Jim McKay Chevrolet,
you'll be setting sail
to the Bahamas, Singapore
or the Caribbean.
Don't worry, no matter your situation,
you will still be setting sail.
It's all okay at Jim McKay.
Whether that's bankruptcy,
divorce, repossession,
bad credit or no credit at all,
with Jim McKay's credit amnesty program,
as long as you make $350
a week, you're approved
for up to $30,000 in
credit for your new ride.
And now, you get a
four-day, three-night cruise
for two to one of three
tropical locations.
Beat the heat relaxing
cool sun on the deck
of a Caribbean cruise.
What do you have to lose?
A new car and a cruise, with Jim McKay's
credit amnesty program,
as long as you make
$350 a week, you're approved
for up to $30,000 in credit.
Spaces are limited, so
call Jim McKay now to get
your new Chevy and reserve your trip.
At best, this offer ends
once the month's over.
Call Jim McKay Chevrolet today!
(upbeat music)
♪ This is where it all begins ♪
♪ 'Cause this could be the
best day of our lives ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ This is where it all begins ♪
- [Narrator] Brushing only
reaches 25% of your mouth.
Listerine cleans virtually 100%.
Helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%,
always go for 100%.
Bring out the bold.
(upbeat music)
- Welcome back to TMZ Live.
It may have been the, well
actually I'm gonna say
was the most menacing news:
O. J. Simpson saying
that he's got some people
to get even with, therefore
he's gonna join Twitter.
He made this big announcement
and then he now has a Twitter account,
and the first, I don't
know if this is someone
he feels he needs to get even with,
but the first thing he
chose to address was,
who is Khloe Kardashian's father.
This has been a long
held rumor that O. J.--
- Unsubstantiated.
- Yes, that O. J. is
Khloe's dad, and I think,
Kris has addressed this
- The family just poo-pooed it
- I think Khloe's addressed it, right.
- They just said come on.
- But O. J. wanted to
give his two cents on it.
Here's what he said and
pay close attention--
- The way he says it.
- It's not so much even
Khloe, it's what he's saying
about Kris.
- Kris.
- Bob Kardashian, he's
like a brother to me,
he's a great guy.
He met and married Kris, they really had
a terrific time together
when they were together.
Unfortunately that ended.
But never, and I wanna
stress never, in any way
shape or form had I ever
had any interest in Kris
romantically or sexually.
And I never got any indication
that she had any interest
in me, so all of these stories
are just bogus, bad, you know tasteless.
Khloe, like all the
girls, I'm very proud of,
just like I know Bob
would be if he was here.
But to simplify to the
matter, is she's not mine.
- This guy, he's so pathetic.
I mean he's just doing
this because the attention
was running low, and here we are again
talking about something
that we already knew
the answer to, but of course,
he just has to try and
lend his voice to it.
- [Both] Yeah.
- I was actually, as I was
listening to what he was saying
what was the thing about
Kris, where he says,
"Look I had no interest
in her whatsoever."
He knows that she didn't
have any interest in him.
- Well no, but that's kind of incidental,
I mean the beginning is "I
had no interest in her."
- Well I disagree that it's incidental,
he said it both ways, he
said "It didn't happen,
"I wasn't in to her".
- [Harvey] And as far as I know.
- "And she never told
me she was into me", so.
- [Charles] It sounds odd,
but it seems honest from O. J.
- [Harvey] But why not just say
"Hey it just didn't happen"?
- [Charles] I don't know.
- [Commentator] Not
only did it not happen--
- [Harvey] Give me more proof!
- But what he's saying is,
"Not only did it not happen that I'm not,
"it's just there was nothing
between us like that."
It's not that there was some
kind of flame that we never acted on,
this was not a thing.
- [Charles] Right.
(commentator mumbles)
- That would be enough.
- The reason it just
feels weird is because,
honestly it's O. J. just being honest.
And that just feels weird.
- It feels weird 'cause,
why are you on Twitter, dog?
- As you were speaking I was just going,
"Wait, what is this end game here?"
- It seems like--
- And you know what
the end game has to be somehow, right?
- What?
- For him, he thinks
it's money.
- Money.
- And somehow he's gonna
get a certain number
of followers and that
somehow he's gonna be able
to translate that into money.
- If anybody should be willing to like,
you know, cut their
losses and just go ahead
and live out the rest of their life
and just virtual obscurity,
it should be O. J.
- It should be O. J.
Don't be trying to get
like a professional deal.
- You could have made that
argument after the murder trial.
- Yes.
- And it just, you know--
- But he refused to, and
you know where it got him.
- Hi, my name is Erica
Chestane, I'm from Georgia.
When these O. J. tweets started
popping up on my timeline,
I didn't know what to think.
And then he said that the Khloe rumors are
bad, bogus and tasteless.
But you can't take something
seriously from a guy
who wrote a book called "If I Did It".
- [Harvey] Yeah, (laughs) right.
- Honestly to me, Khloe
pre-op looks just like O. J.
And if you put a picture of Sydney Simpson
up against Khloe Kardashian pre-op,
it's undeniable.
It's like they're twins.
- So, Melissa, sorry, Erica.
- It's deniable.
- So Erica, you just came on here
and you're just gonna
completely start this up again?
Like everybody involved has shot it down.
- People look like other
people, and also Sydney Simpson,
I mean, that would be a different mother,
so none of them, it
just doesn't make sense.
- And how many times are
you gonna say pre-op?
That's like the game, man.
(Charles laughing)
That's all I heard, that's shady, dog.
- A lot of shade, a lot of shade.
We're gonna move on.
(upbeat music)
- Mafia rules do not
apply for George Lopez
when dealing with President Trump.
You know Mafia rules, you
leave women and children out.
- [Harvey] That's true.
- Right, because George is going after
the first family,
and specifically on the
immigration policies
of the administration,
and says that he has no issues
dragging children into it.
I get that the President
has older adult children,
but even Barron.
This is the post that George Lopez put up,
and made the point of
including Barron in there.
Barron who is 13 years
old, and making it clear
that he's from an immigrant mother.
- [Harvey] Right.
- [Charles] (laughs) And that actually all
of his children also, his first
wife, also an immigrant so--
- [Harvey] Not all maples, not Tiffany.
- No, you're right, Tiffany
is not included there.
So yes, calling them all anchor babies.
So we got George out 'cause
a lot of people feel like,
look, obviously people are very critical
of the immigration
policy, that's one thing.
But when you start bringing, you know,
minor children into it.
- Kids, yeah.
- [Charles] Does it cross the line?
- So we got him out.
- Yeah.
- [Interviewer] Do you think
it's fair to put Barron
in that post?
(laughs)
- Why?
- [Interviewer] He's a kid, you know.
- Is it fair to put kids in cages?
They're kids.
Let's go Ancestry.com and 23andMe,
so everybody's swabbing
the insides of their mouth
to find out where they came from,
and you know what we can all agree on?
Is that nobody is from here.
Immigration has always been a problem
and it will continue to be a problem,
but only targeting Latinos is not good.
- [Harvey] So you know who
would disagree with him?
- Who's that?
- The Obamas.
They made it very clear.
- Children--
- During the presidency
that unless, you know,
Sasha and Malia were part of an event
where, you know,
- Right.
- they were there.
- They did not want them to be
- They really were against
them even being photographed,
because they said they
didn't sign up for this.
I think they would disagree with that.
- I think a lot of presidential families
actually would disagree with it.
I think the Clintons
would disagree with it
because they also fought
for privacy for Chelsea
because she was in the limelight as well
during their presidency and
faced a lot of, you know,
undue attention and a lot
of criticism, meanness,
and this was before the
era of social media.
But of course I think what
George is referring to,
you know here by targeting
Donald Trump's children,
is again sort of all of the
actions that have been taken
by the administration against
children at the border.
Putting them in cages.
So, I mean, I think the point
that he's trying to make,
you know, might be a valid one,
but it's using people that
is unfair, in unfair way.
- Here's the thing.
He could make the point
just with Donald Jr.
and Eric and Ivanka.
He doesn't have to go to Barron.
- [Charles] You don't
have to go to Barron.
- And that's why it's
a little problematic.
- Hey guys, how you
doin', my name's Dominic.
This issue is a little pressing.
I would say instead of
targeting Barron Trump,
he includes him.
In a way yes, he's wrong for
you to include the family,
but to compare the Obamas and the Clintons
to the Trumps is literally
comparing apples to oranges.
- I don't think it is,
I gotta stop you there.
- Could you erase politics--
- Yeah.
- And just say it's about--
- It's about a family
with minor kids.
- Right.
- And the issue is do
you, because once you,
look, here's the thing.
This country is divided
almost down the middle,
so whatever you allow on this side,
this side's gonna do.
So, at a point you have to have a policy.
If the policy is minor
kids are not fair game,
then they're not fair game on either side.
But if they're fair game on one side,
they're gonna be fair
game on the other side.
- Right.
- I mean, it's just
the way it works.
- 'Cause you gotta look at
it without the politics.
- Right, okay, taking a break.
(upbeat music)
- Stay with us for live team coverage
of this developing story.
- We have exclusive new details
coming into the FOX 5 Newsroom.
- Tracking temperatures
now across the region,
looks like big changes ahead for tomorrow.
(upbeat music)
- This is gonna be big.
- My Caleb Sofa & Loveseat,
with Bob's Discount,
you get both pieces for just 799.
- 799, are you joking?
- Do I look like I'm joking?
- Yes, you look like you're joking.
- I'm serious.
- Cool.
- [Crowd] Get Bob's Discount.
- The best way to get to the beach.
- [Narrator] With Neutrogena
Beach Defense sunscreen.
Helioplex powered, UVA/UVB strong.
Beach strength protection
for the whole family.
- For the best day in the sun.
(water splashes)
Neutrogena.
(inspiring music)
- For many years,
I've just never liked my backside,
Very square, it's just
not attractive at all.
Now, it's like a new lease of life.
Dr. Jones exceeded my expectations.
I am so happy, I just love him.
- I'm Dr. Michael Jones,
the founder of Lexington Plastic Surgeons.
And our surgeons strive
to make sure that all
of our patients leave the door looking
and feeling their very best.
- [Narrator] Lexington Plastic Surgeons.
Changing lives for the
better one patient at a time.
- Popeyes' new Parmesan
Ranch Double Dippers.
Nice move.
- He's double dipping.
- Ranch and Parmesan.
- Do you guys wanna try some of this?
- [Narrator] Now you can double dip
six boneless wings with my $5
Parmesan Ranch Double Dippers
♪ No bad chicken from Popeyes ♪
- We have to be able to repair
the enamel on a daily basis.
With the new Pronamel repair toothpaste,
we can help actively repair
enamel in its weakened state.
It's innovative.
My go-to toothpaste is
gonna be Pronamel repair.
(horror music)
(screams)
- Having kids means having stuff.
My Keystone Stairway Bunk.
Storage inside the
stairs, behind the stairs,
even under the bed in
gray, espresso or white.
Only 777.
- [Crowd] Get Bob's Discount.
(dramatic music)
- I have a contract.
- I don't care.
People who are not
licensed daycare providers
shouldn't be taking
care of infants, period.
- [Narrator] Next Judge Judy.
Today at four and 4:30 on FOX 5.
- [Narrator] FOX 5 DC on Twitter.
- They gone to the dog house!
- Oh my.
- [Narrator] Watch, follow, engage.
(dramatic music)
♪ You won't stop us ♪
(upbeat music)
- Welcome back to TMZ
Live, Harvey and Van here.
- What up.
- I'm really excited
about this show today,
I mean this is great.
I love John Ratzenberger.
- Ah man.
- I just love
John Ratzenberger.
- I know one reason why you love him,
and I'm gonna say this
because you like people
who are talented, but you also like people
who have two different distinct acts.
- Yes, that's exactly right.
- John Ratzenberger
was on "Cheers", huge show.
- Huge star.
- Biggest show on television.
And now, to be in every
single Pixar movie,
and has a fantastic
second career doing that.
- I love that, I love that.
Well speaking of, Toy
Story 4 sounds amazing,
I mean the cast is amazing.
And there is kind of a
posthumous character on this.
- [Van] Right.
- So, I can't wait to bring him in.
John, welcome to TMZ Live.
- Thank you, thanks for that nice intro.
- Well, it's well deserved.
So, a lot of people were shocked
because everybody thought
maybe Toy Story 3 was the end,
So this is a huge surprise.
- [John] Yeah, I wouldn't
be surprised if they did
a fifth one, to tell you the truth.
- [Van] Really?
- It might not be done in my lifetime,
but somewhere down the line.
- How long did it take to do?
- What, Toy Story 4?
I think it took 'em about
three to four years somewhere.
- Gosh that it a big investment.
You know, I love the cast,
I mean in addition to
you, you got Tom Hanks,
you've got Tim Allen.
I love that Tony Hale is in the show.
He's so funny, he was
so amazing on "Veep".
- Yeah, the way they see him on this,
I think he's the funniest
character in the movie.
(mumbles) The character
he plays is hysterical.
- John, I gotta ask you something,
I saw Toy Story 3,
and of course it was a phenomenal
movie, made huge money,
broke all kinds of records.
But at the end, it was sad,
it was a very, very sad tough watch.
There were people in the theater
crying and stuff like that.
There are people out there,
parents who are concerned
about bringing their kids to the movie
if it's gonna be that sad.
Does this one have kind of the same tenor
as Toy Story 3, or is it
a little bit different?
- Well, so the kids don't have to wait
'till their grandfather dies, you know.
(Harvey and Van laugh hysterically)
It'll give 'em a chance to work through
the sadness at an early age.
(Harvey and Van laughing)
It's not that sad, it's
sad but it's not that sad.
- So, that's hilarious.
Don Rickles, you know, he
played Mr. Potato Head.
He passed in 2017.
You guys brought him back.
- Well yeah, yeah Josh did, the director.
He searched for hours
and hours over old tape
that they had for Don
in the other Toy Stories
and of some promos he did.
So he cobbled together
Don's part from those tapes.
- [Van] That is actually amazing.
- It's amazing.
John, I just gotta ask
you 'cause what Van said
at the beginning is so right.
I mean, you've just had
the most incredible career.
I'm just curious about when
you finished with "Cheers",
'cause there's so many people
who think it'll never
get bigger than this--
- [Van] How could you go out of "Cheers"?
- Yeah.
And it's like just personally,
did you think that?
Was it shocking to you?
Did you kind of expect it all along?
I'm just dying to know
what was in your head,
you know, at the end of that run.
- Well, every day was a gift from God,
I mean you had to pinch yourself
'cause your job description was,
you sit at a bar, crack
jokes, and get paid for it.
I mean that's, talk about
the luckiest people on earth,
and then I get a call from John Lasseter
25 years ago saying,
"Do you wanna play a pig
"in a cartoon movie?"
That's it, 25 years now I've
been working with Pixar.
- So, Pixar is the most
successful film studio
of all time, you are in every Pixar movie.
John, are you the most
successful actor of all time?
(John laughs)
- Why would you laugh at that?
- Why you laughin'?
- [Harvey] I wouldn't laugh at that, John.
- [Van] I think you've
got a solid case my G!
- I'm just thinking of
images of Spencer Tracy
and John Malkovich popped up in my head.
(laughing)
- [Harvey] I mean.
- Box office-wise I think
I'm number three though.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- [Van] Who's one and two?
- I don't know.
- Oh I know, Samuel L.
Jackson I think is one.
- Sam's got to be up
there, certainly, yeah.
- Wow, we got a top five star.
- I know, I'm so excited.
- Of all time
on our show, man.
- I'm so excited.
Hey John, listen, we're thrilled for you.
It really is an honor to have you on,
and congratulations, it's enormous.
So just congratulations
on all your success
over many, many years.
- Thank you, thank you very much.
I appreciate that.
- You're amazing.
Thank you John.
- Cheers brother.
- [Harvey] We're gonna take a break.
(upbeat music)
- [Astronaut] Go for landing, over.
(beeps)
Roger anything, go for
landing, 3,000 feet.
Yeah, looking good.
(beeps)
- [Narrator] Discover a new world,
right here on this one.
Luray Caverns, what will you discover?
(happy music)
- [Narrator] People aren't talking about
how Giant's fresh Chesapeake Bay seafood
is 100% sustainable.
They're not talking about
how our local products
are sourced from over
40 family-owned farms.
Or how we carry local dry
aged steaks and burgers.
They're not talking
because they're eating.
Mm, looks delicious.
At Giant, we believe in local
because it's about offering
fresh food you love
from the place you call home.
The little things are Giant.
- You've tried so many moisturizers.
(water splashes)
But one blows them all out of the water.
Hydro Boost with hyaluronic
acid to plump skin cells
so it bounces back.
Neutrogena.
And try our hydrating make up.
- [Narrator] You want new furniture now
and you want it for less?
There's only one place to go.
Price Busters Furniture's
4th of July sale.
With huge saving storewide
and low, low payments.
Seven-piece living room just
$19 payments with zero down.
Complete nine-piece
bedroom with free mattress
just $19 payments with zero down.
Save now, get it now, and pay later!
That's right, buy with no money down.
Nothing, period!
Plus get free delivery.
This 4th of July, Price Busters Furniture
saves you money, lots of money!
(happy music)
- Buy one, take one is back.
Starting at just 12.99 at Olive Garden.
Join us for a new favorite today,
then bring one home for tomorrow on us.
Buy one, take one for a limited
time only at Olive Garden.
(dramatic music)
- [Announcer] Attention riders,
get ready to take your
vocal cords to new heights.
Prepare your taste buds for
the time of their lives.
Remain seated while the hairs on the back
of your neck stand up.
And please, enjoy the ride.
(happy music)
- [Narrator] Get the best deal on tickets
at KingsDominion.com.
Kings Dominion, it's amazing in here.
(playful music)
- [Narrator] These kids just discovered
an all-natural version
of a video game classic.
Luray Caverns, what will you discover?
(upbeat music)
- Welcome back to TMZ Live,
if you showed up for
something called Skankfest.
(laughs)
- That is the name.
- It's a comedy festival,
Skankfest Comedy Mayhem.
It's a festival in Brooklyn,
you got a big surprise
because there was a
performer that no one knew
was gonna be there,
in fact we're told really the organizer.
- Yeah, that was it.
- It was the only person
who pulled this off,
and then announced that,
"Surprise, Louis C.K. is here".
- So what kind of reaction
do you think he got?
I would have anticipated
a really strong reaction
because in the comedy circuit,
he's always gotten that.
- This is a festival that was just about
comedians for three days, so--
- And you know that he--
- If you're there, you're a diehard
comedy fan.
- There were issues that
came up with him.
- When he made a surprise
appearance a few months ago.
- No, no I'm just saying
that the backstory
of this whole thing.
- That's the back story of course.
- Which you probably heard.
- Louis, you know, masturbating
in front of people,
and you know he lost--
- He lost a lot of gigs.
- A lot of gigs, he lost a movie.
So, he's been trying he's been doing
these appearances every now
and then to mixed reactions.
So here's what happened.
- [Announcer] Skankfest
is a cool event, right?
You never know what can happen.
Crazy things can happen.
Here's one of those crazy things.
Ladies and gentlemen, Louis C.K.!
(crowd cheering)
- [Crowd] Louis, Louis, Louis, Louis!
- [Harvey] This went on for a long time.
- [Charles] Long ovation,
and so you can't even say
that's mixed, I mean, that is--
- [Harvey] It was not mixed.
- That is as, it's as full throated
an ovation he's gonna get.
- Yeah, it's a pretty shocking response.
I mean it almost sounds like, you know,
the audience's favorite
team just won a game
(laughs) or something like that.
- [Charles] Well I would
say for a lot of people
in that crowd, Louis before
anything happened, remember,
was on top of the comedy world.
- Right.
- So this was,
you know, for diehard comedy fans,
they would've probably
been jonesing to see
Louis C.K. perform again.
That's, I think, why
you got that reaction,
and I don't know if going
forward this will help him,
but we're told the people who were there
that he actually did open with a joke,
or I don't know if it's a joke,
but he referred to his--
- Yeah, he opened the set by saying
if you ever masturbate
in front of someone,
ask them first, and if they say yes,
- Don't do it.
- don't do it.
- By the way, I don't
know if you saw this,
but Roseanne is performing
in Atlantic City.
- Yep, with--
- And the same name.
Yeah, that this is again what we talked
about with snapshots and whatnot.
- That you cannot--
- So we'll see.
I mean, who was that again?
- Andrew Dice Clay, yeah.
- Andrew Dice Clay,
that's right.
- That's an interesting double builder.
- Hi, this is Sarah Butler
from Des Moines, Iowa.
- Hi Sarah. (laughs)
- Hey, I think he's doing
what he does best, comedy.
I mean he may have made a mistake,
and done some things
some people don't like
but gettin' right back into,
you know, the business,
what he loves to do and what he's good at,
and he's good at making people laugh.
So, I mean I think he
should've gone right back.
- [Harvey] Yeah, and the
audience received him well.
- It was when they were gonna forgive,
and it sounds like it's there.
- [Harvey] We're gonna take a break.
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
- Start the car!
Start the car!
- [Narrator] The IKEA Summer Sale.
- Woo!
- [Narrator] Save up
to 50% off select items
in store only June 26th to July 7th.
IKEA.
- [Narrator] Happy 4th of July.
Call now and save with Bath Fitter.
UP to $600 off your
tub and shower upgrade.
If you need a place to relax,
or a conversion to make bathing easier,
count on the company
with a lifetime warranty.
And installation in as little as one day.
But don't wait, call today and find out
why Bath Fitter is the perfect fit.
♪ Call Bath Fitter ♪
♪ We're the perfect fit ♪
- [Narrator] Connect
with everything you love
online with Cox Internet.
Call today to get Cox Internet,
starting at only 29.99 a month.
Stream all your favorite shows
with up to one GIG speeds
available everywhere.
Plus, get Panoramic Wifi that blasts
super fast internet all over your home.
Stay connected with Cox
Internet starting at just
29.99 a month for up to 10 Mbps.
Call today.
- Hi, my name is Geoffrey Tade,
and I have lost 78 pounds in 93 days
with Dr. Cory Aplin's weight loss program.
I have more energy now
than I've ever had before.
I can go back and wear my old clothing.
I no longer have any hypoglycemic episodes
like I once had.
- Hi, I'm Dr. Aplin.
To find out how you can
lose up to a pound of fat
per day, call this number right now
for your no obligation consultation.
(sad piano music)
- [Narrator] You're a
person, not a credit score.
But sometimes, your score gets in the way
of the things you want to do.
Personal consumer loans through NetCredit,
help you borrow up to $10,000.
And, you can check if you're
eligible at NetCredit.com
without affecting your credit score.
You may even be able to
build your credit history
as you repay.
NetCredit, a more personal personal loan.
Visit NetCredit.com today.
(upbeat music)
(camera shutter clicking)
♪ Body talk ♪
(upbeat music)
- Welcome back to TMZ Live.
Marc Anthony passionately singing
"I Will Always Love
You" to Jennifer Lopez.
- That's weird.
- That seems weird, right?
Especially because A-Rod was
sitting right between them.
Actually he was passionately singing,
but this was an event for
Marc and Jennifer's kids,
and Alex is there of course now.
And he posted a video
that shows everybody's
getting along just fine.
♪ I will always ♪
♪ Love you ♪
- [Charles] I thought,
this was one of their,
I don't know which one of their kids
was having a choir concert.
- You know, you really have to commend
Marc Anthony and J. Lo for, you know,
getting along as well as they do.
But you know, in order to
bring in another person
into that relationship,
it honestly could mess everything up.
But you know what, A-Rod is a great dude.
It looks like he's having a great time.
It looks like him and
Marc Anthony are bros.
- [Harvey] Good for them.
- Good for them.
- Will it work?
- [Charles] Everything works for them.
We will see you next time.
(upbeat music)
- I'm a lawyer.
(camera shutter clicks)
(jingling)
- Everyone wants to buy houses these days.
But whom can you trust?
Call Express Homebuyers,
thousands of homeowners
have trusted us to buy their
house the hassle-free way.
♪ Express Homebuyers ♪
♪ We buy your house in seven days ♪
- After my car accident, I didn't know
that a lawyer would help deal
with all of my medical bills.
- I didn't know I could also get money
for pain and suffering.
- I didn't know the
insurance company wasn't
going to give me the
settlement I deserved.
- We do know.
At Saiontz & Kirk, we know injury law
and we know how to get you
the most money possible.
- Clients of Saiontz & Kirk have collected
over $1 billion.
- When you need a lawyer,
you have a lawyer.
- Call 1-800-LAWYERS or
visit YouHaveALawyer.com.
If you have a phone, you have a lawyer.
- We are sisters.
- And we just moved in together.
- [Narrator] Why Alissa
and Aleah chose Fios.
- We stream so much.
- A lot of times, Alissa is watching TV,
on her laptop, using her
phone, also using her tablet.
- I am really good at multi-tasking.
'Cause I'm awesome.
- A little.
(both laughing)
- [Narrator] The best
internet is even better
at our best price.
Switch now and get our
faster speeds available.
Plus a free Chromebook on us.
That's Fios.
- The only thing thing that
I would do differently.