(upbeat music)
- We have a fairly widespread
winter weather advisory.
(upbeat music)
(bright music)
(energetic music)
- [Announcer] Today on TMZ...
- This is clearly the
roll-up to the Grammys,
and Beyonce is skating there.
- [Katie] Janelle Monáe
had a roller skating party
and her guest of honor was Beyonce.
- I'm just thinking people actually
go out during the weekdays?
- Celebrities don't go out on the weekend.
They go out during the week.
- If you don't have a real job,
it's better to party on those days.
- I can't go out, like, on
a Tuesday, a Monday night,
with everybody else.
I have to be at work everyday.
- You also have two
young children at home!
- You have children, Raquel.
- Ariana Grande is calling
the producer of the Grammys a liar.
The producer, Ken Ehrlich,
said that Ariana pulled out
because she was too frazzled
and couldn't get a decent
performance together in time.
Ariana is pissed.
She even tweeted:
"I can pull together a
performance overnight
"and you know that, Ken."
- When you say the name
Ken, you're really mad.
Dammit, Ken, you know that about me.
(group laughs)
- We got Matt Gaetz.
He is Republican, a
representative from Florida.
And when we say people are calling you
the conservative
Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez...
- [Reporter] You think you guys could be
a power couple together?
- I don't know.
That might be a little presumptuous of me,
but I would certainly swipe
right on the opportunity.
- He's incredibly charming in this video.
- He represents Pensacola, Florida,
which is very conservative.
- Fun fact, Pensacola,
Florida has the most
whitest sandest beaches
in the United States.
- Pensacola, even the beaches are white.
(group laughs)
- Jen Selter hit up the beaches of Cabo
in this really cute bikini.
She looks incredible.
- Hey, you know what?
She's been a little bit thirsty
because today the weather is 22 degrees.
- That's Celsius.
(group laughs)
- Oh.
(intense music)
♪ TMZ kidz ♪
♪ Let's have fun with-- ♪
- [Announcer] TMZ daddies!
Oh, yeah.
Goo-goo, ga-ga,
Conor McGregor.
- Conor McGregor just looks so good.
- He's got a great body and his swagger.
- [Announcer] He's got so much swagger,
even the waves can't knock him down.
Now, who's the party pooper?
- No, the swim diaper keeps
all the boo-boo inside.
- [Announcer] Good to know.
So, who's the kid?
- He's with Conor, Junior,
his firstborn sun.
It was a warm, winter day in Miami.
- Aw.
- [Announcer] Yep, Conor spent
an idyllic day by the sea
with his one-year-old son,
a little too idyllic if you ask this guy.
- Is this, um, orchestrated?
- Naw, Conor takes his son everywhere.
He took his son to the Superbowl.
- [Announcer] Yeah, he likes...
Being seen with his adorable child.
Wait a minute!
- It's interesting,
because it is a way of softening
his image after the dolly.
- [Announcer] As in the
dolly Conor hurled at a bus
causing painful injuries to
a fellow UFC fighter's face?
And speaking of faces,
it's like Conor's looking into a mirror.
Oh!
- Right now, it's very chilly out here.
If you can afford it,
why not go to Miami where
it's in the high 70s?
- He's from Ireland.
- That's even worse than L.A.
That's negative, probably, like who knows?
- I want to open my phone day
and have it say negative who knows.
- Oh my God, that's I need a jacket,
it's negative probably who knows.
- And then you open it up,
it says hot as fish grease.
(group laughs)
- [Announcer] Happy dadding!
Daddy.
- Kim Kardashian was
on Jimmy Fallon's show
and was talking all about her fourth kid,
but you really couldn't concentrate
because she was so freaking gorgeous
in this like skintight snakeskin dress.
I know we say this all the time,
but it really is the
best she's ever looked.
- She looks amazing every day.
It's ridiculous.
- How long does it take Kim
Kardashian to get ready?
- Hours.
Hours.
- Oh God, to sit there.
- Why do you care about sitting there?
Someone's pampering and you're drinking.
Who cares?
- The worst.
It would just drive me crazy.
- How long does it take you to get ready?
- 11 minutes.
- You time yourself?
- Uh-huh, I know exact,
because I have to time
myself in the morning.
- What do you do at the 11th minute?
What's the last, like, ugh!
- Do you wink at yourself?
- The last one is you got this, Levin.
(group laughs)
(intense music)
- [Announcer] It's one of the
biggest feuds in Hollywood.
Ariana Grande versus this guy!
Who the hell is that, Richard Dreyfus?
- Ariana Grande is calling the producer
of the Grammys a liar.
- Oh, it's Ken Ehrlich
who did an interview saying Ariana Grande,
whose face has been used everywhere
to promote the Grammys this year,
won't be performing after all
because he claims she felt it was, quote,
"too late for her to pull
something together," unquote.
And now Ariana is clapping
back Pelosi-style,
calling Ehrlich a liar, liar McLiarson.
- She said, "I've kept my mouth shut,
"but now you're lying about me.
"I can pull together a
performance overnight,
"and you know that, Ken."
- [Announcer] According to Ariana,
she wanted to sing her hit
song Japanese barbecue,
AKA 7 rings,
but Ken didn't think the
audience would relate,
to which Ariana said, thank you, next.
So, who do we believe?
- I am 100% Team Ariana.
- Nah.
- They are putting her
everywhere, her face everywhere,
because they want her audience
to come to the Grammys.
- 7 rings is the number one
song in the country right now.
That doesn't make any sense to me.
- Who do we know all this from?
- I know it.
- Do we have Ken's comment?
- What Ken says is that
she was too frazzled
to pull it together.
- Right, and it's not true.
Did you see the statement?
- From whom?
- Ken!
- [Announcer] Guys, guys!
Calm down.
Perhaps we need some estrogen
to clear this all up.
- They only let you perform
songs that are nominated.
That song is not nominated.
(group cheers)
- [Announcer] You tell 'em, girl.
Except for one thing.
- Last year at the Grammys,
Childish Gambino performed a
song that was not nominated
and so did Sam Smith.
- [Announcer] Women, right?
Hey, at least they tried.
We'll miss you at the
Grammys this year, Ariana.
Well, maybe Ken won't, but you know.
Everyone else will.
(energetic music)
- I love you, beard.
(audience laughs)
- [Producer] Julian Edelman's
playoff beard is no more.
- [Harvey] Oh, you're kidding.
He finally shaved it off.
- And it's because of Ellen DeGeneres.
So, Julian Edelman had this epic beard.
He's been growing it nine months,
so it's around training camp time.
He went on Ellen DeGeneres,
and she said I'll donate $10,000
to the Boys and Girls Club.
- But you need to let me
shave that beard first.
- Let's do it.
Let's do it.
- Yay!
(audience cheers)
- So, how does he look after it?
- [Blond Man] So, he's
actually a very beautiful man.
- [Female Staff Member] He's so hot.
Oh my God, he's so hot.
- [Male Crew Member] Is he
hotter with the beard or without?
- [Female Staff Member] Without.
He's so hot.
- [Harvey] Yeah, he's great-looking.
- Everybody's hotter with a beard.
- I agree.
- That's not true.
- Not true at all.
- Everybody's better with a beard.
- No.
- Yes, girls love,
like, a George Michael overgrow.
- That's not true!
Stop saying what we like.
- Julian Edelman looks
a million times better
without a beard.
- No, not at all.
No, beards.
Beards, man.
- No, that's not true.
- Believe me, man.
Girls like beards.
- I don't.
- No.
- Not true.
- Girls like beards
because a baby face means--
- Stop telling us what girls like.
(group laughs)
- Girls like beards.
(audience cheering)
(upbeat music)
(intense music)
- [Reporter] Congressman
Gaetz, how you doing, man?
- Good.
- [Announcer] Fellow Americans,
say hello to Republican
congressman Matt Gaetz
from the great state of Florida.
- Super conservative, I believe.
- Very conservative,
very much about the wall.
- [Announcer] In fact,
many are calling him
the conservative Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez.
- Well, that is totally unfair.
AOC is way more interesting and attractive
and capable than I am.
- He said capable?
- Capable.
- Did he just sandwich that attractive in?
- Literally right in between the two.
- [Announcer] Ooh, well,
maybe you can get Rashida
to pass her a note during session.
But you two are so different!
For instance, she likes dancing,
and you try to get parents
of Parkland victims
kicked out of a congressional hearing.
Listen, the biggest
difference in this town
isn't whether people are
Republicans or Democrats.
It's whether they want to
shake the place up or not.
She does, and I admire her for it.
- [Announcer] Wow, I don't
remember any congressperson
ever saying that about another
congressperson that way.
- Republicans, like, usually their line is
she's young and stupid.
Like, that's what's always
their criticism of her.
- Sometimes, haters just gotta hate, man,
and that's not what I'm about.
- [Announcer] So, what
is Matt Gaetz about?
Well, he's extremely pro-gun,
but is also pro-marijuana,
which means you can be prepared
for the zombie apocalypse but
won't care when it happens.
Say, you know who else is pro-marijuana?
AOC.
- I would certainly swipe
right on the opportunity
to write a cannabis bill with her.
- [Announcer] Dude.
(group groans)
- [All] No.
- Are you kidding me?
- I think would it help America
if those guys, like, started dating.
They seem like Romeo and Juliet
a little bit, don't they?
- [Announcer] And that turned out great.
- If he does take a chance on
pissing off his electorate,
he represents Pensacola, Florida,
which is very conservative.
- Wait, fun fact.
Pensacola, Florida has the
most whitest sandest beaches
in the United States.
- Pensacola, even the beaches are white.
(all laugh)
- [Reporter] Thanks, Congressman.
- [Announcer] Politics!
(intense music)
- Jen Selter,
super popular Instagram model,
hit up the beaches of Cabo
in this really cute bikini.
She looks incredible.
- She was like the OG butt girl,
and now I, I don't even know
what the hell happened to her.
- Jen Selter is still big.
- I disagree.
- We haven't heard from her in a while.
- She has 13 million Instagram followers.
She just launched a whole, like,
fitness diet plan and everything.
She's doing great.
- [Patrick] If you have 13
million Instagram followers,
you can make hundreds
of thousands of dollars
advertising products on Instagram.
She's doing really, really well.
Much better than most of
the other Instagram models.
- Hey, you know what?
She's being a little bit thirsty,
because today the weather is 22 degrees.
(group laughs)
- That's Celsius.
- Oh.
(laughs)
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Coming up...
- Janelle Monáe threw the
best pre-Grammy party.
She did a retro rollerskating party.
Her guest of honor was Beyonce,
so we have video of
Beyonce roller-skating.
- You're, like, out of breath.
- I'm so excited!
- [Announcer] Plus, Patrick
Whitesell, the super agent.
- Who introduced Jeff
Bezos to his wife Lauren.
- [Charles] We got him out last night.
Nice guy, and he was with--
- [Harvey] Hot model.
- But that's a subtle message.
He's that nice guy.
- How's that a subtle message?
- He's the nice guy in the situation.
- Oh my God.
- You are an idiot.
(group laughs)
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] TMZ brought
to you by TJ Maxx.
It's not shopping, it's maximizing.
- [TJ Maxx Narrator] This is you shopping.
And this is you maximizing at TJ Maxx.
You shopping.
You maximizing.
Find the brands you love and
get more you for your money
every time.
It's not shopping.
It's maximizing.
Start maximizing today.
Max life at TJ Maxx.
- [Announcer] Coming up.
- Danielle Bregoli had her own show
come out on Snapchat.
- If I had to put my money on
a 15-year-old becoming rich and famous...
- She's already rich and famous.
(group laughs)
- [Announcer] Be right back.
- [Fox 5 Narrator] Sunday mornings,
Fox 5 takes a deep dive into
the top political headlines.
Join Tom Fitzgerald as we break
down the weekend politics.
Fox 5 News On the Hill.
- I could hear men's thoughts.
- [Shaq] (crunching)
Pretzels are delicious.
- [Movie Announcer] Get ready
for the comedy event of the year.
- He slept with your cousin Gabby.
- He said you were on a break.
- Everybody lying.
(crowd gasps)
- Amen.
- [Movie Announcer] What
Men Want, now playing.
Rated R.
- [Planet Fitness Announcer]
It's the No Commitment Sale
at Planet Fitness.
For just 25¢ down,
$10 a month with no commitment,
you'll get tons of cardio
and strength equipment,
free fitness training,
and a totally comfortable
place to go at your happy pace.
Get all this for just 25¢ down,
$10 a month, no commitment.
Now is the right time to join.
Join in-club or online
at planetfitness.com.
Planet Fitness, the judgment-free zone.
- [Terms Narrator] Join Planet Fitness
for only 25¢ down, $10 a
month with no commitment.
Now through February 12th.
- When I walked through a
snowstorm for a cigarette,
that's when I knew I had to quit
for real this time.
That's why I'm using Nicorette.
- [Nicorette Narrator] Only Nicorette Gum
has patented dual-coated
technology for great taste
plus intense craving relief.
- Every great why needs a great how.
- [Theraflu Narrator]
New Theraflu PowerPods,
the cold and flu fighting
machine you put in your machine.
Press the button to
brew up powerful relief
to defeat your toughest
cold and flu symptoms fast.
New Theraflu PowerPods.
Press, sip, relief.
- [Toyota Announcer]
It's time to go Toyota
with the strongest lineup
of Toyota trucks ever.
Go Tacoma right now with 1,000 cash back.
The leader in versatility and
built for off-road adventure.
Go with Tundra and get 1,500 cash back,
or pick a 4Runner with rugged
body-on-frame construction,
and if you want to kick it up a notch,
check out the TRD Pro Series.
Go reliable, go Toyota,
and let's go places.
- [JCPenney Announcer] At the JCPenney
Valentine's Day Sale,
there's more to love.
Take an extra 20% off with
your JCPenney credit card
and coupon
and get up to 70% off
fine jewelry after coupon.
Or for for $25, shop diamond jewelry
or a Sephora Favorites perfume sampler.
Great gifts meet prices.
JCPenney.
- [Judge Judy Narrator]
A vacation interrupted
by a bad rental?
- She retained $891.50.
- That is not true.
I did not.
- Don't talk to anybody else.
- I didn't understand
when I could interject.
- Never.
Do you take something
that makes you hyper?
- I'm just naturally hyper. (laughs)
- [Judge Judy Narrator] Judge Judy.
Monday at four and 4:30 on Fox 5.
(intense music)
(energetic music)
- [Reporter] What's going on, Janelle?
- [Announcer] That's
singer-songwriter Janelle Monáe
attending a pre-grammy
awards party in L.A.
Repping her potential album of the year--
- Dirty Computer.
- [Announcer] Right.
But it was Janelle's pre-grammy
party of the same name
that really had people spinning.
- She did a retro rollerskating party,
and her guest of honor was Beyonce.
- [Announcer] Oh, yeah!
There's Queen Bey getting her swerves on
all over the rink.
- Beyonce.
So, we have video of
Beyonce rollerskating.
- You're like out of breath.
- I'm so excited,
because Janelle Monáe and
Beyonce rollerskating?
It's so cool.
- [Announcer] Damn right.
Beyonce's rocking lucky number seven.
Janelle's rocking
you're-gonna-get-lucky skintight pants.
Model Shaun Ross, Transparent
actress Trace Lysette.
- We have video of her rollerskating?
- [Announcer] Uh, we kinda just showed it.
- Beyonce just thought it was
like an average Thursday night
happening to be like
Janelle Monáe's party.
- Celebrities don't go out on the weekend.
They go out during the week.
That's why I'm pretty much wack now
because I can't go out, like,
on a Tuesday and Monday nights,
like Ace of Diamonds and things like that.
I have to be at work every day.
- You also have two
young children at home.
- You have children, Raquel.
- [Announcer] Oh, that's it.
Alexa, watch children.
Gotta roll!
(intense music)
- I went from sleeping
on the floor in a trailer
to having a gold record in six months.
- Danielle Bregoli is breaking records,
so she had her own show come
out on Snapchat this week,
and it's called Bringing up Bhabie.
This thing killed it.
On the very first day, it
got over 10 million views.
Snapchat even said
if you compare this to Keeping
Up with the Kardashians,
Keeping Up with the Kardashians
gets about 1.5 million views.
- She's a hit.
- She's supposed to make 10
million dollars this year.
- If I had to put my
money on a 15-year-old
becoming rich and famous,
she's gonna be in the top five.
- Well, she's already rich and famous.
- So, that's a pretty good win.
(group laughs)
- You really went out on a limb.
- But you also helped her out a lot.
We picture her every other day.
Every time that we talk about
a lot of people, though,
a nobody, we help them out so much,
it's insane.
- And guess what they do
after they get famous?
- Don't talk to us.
- Exactly.
- You know what happens when
they stop being famous, though?
- We stop talking to them.
So.
- Ha!
- So, we'll talk to anybody.
- That's the party line.
(group laughs)
(intense music)
- [Announcer] And now,
As the Bezos Turns.
Money,
wiener pics,
Amazon,
dating,
Bezos.
Yes, it's been a crazy week
for the richest man in the world,
but now, new drama.
His new girlfriend's estranged
husband is dating this chick.
Wait, we've got a better photo.
Oh, right.
- Patrick Whitesell,
the super agent from
William Morris Endeavor--
- Also known as Lauren
Sanchez's estranged husband.
- [Announcer] Right, because
he was married to her
and friends with him
and introduced her to him
and now they're together.
- But Patrick is okay because
we got him out last night
and he was with hot
model named Keira Alexa,
but they did the thing where
they walk out separately.
- And then get in the
same car in the backseat.
- [Announcer] Slick move, guys.
Now tell us about this hot lady!
- Her name is Keira Alexa.
She's a model, and that's
all I know about her.
- [Announcer] Thanks for
that detailed report.
We'll take it from here.
She loves to sell cookies,
wear bras,
and also not wear bras.
Oh, and she looks a lot
like Patrick's ex Lauren.
- She's roughly 25 years
younger than Lauren.
- [Announcer] That explains the cookies.
- Does it bother Lauren?
Probably a little bit.
- No, Lauren is with Jeff Bezos.
- [Announcer] Speaking of,
he's got some drama of his own
with that whole--
- Your semi-erect manhood
pressing against your zipper.
- [Announcer] We were
gonna say extortion claims,
but thanks for getting specific.
- So, the interesting thing now
is American Media's now saying oops,
we're gonna investigate
ourselves in this thing,
because Jeff Bezos says
they tried blackmailing him.
- The emails were crazy.
- Why would National Enquirer
go get the richest man.
Like, that's just dumb.
- [Announcer] Well, let's
break it down in detail.
- There's a whole bunch of stuff.
- [Announcer] Right, so.
Good luck, Jeff.
And Patrick?
You already got lucky.
(intense music)
- Good news, everybody.
My new movie came out today.
I don't know if you guys noticed,
but I'm starring in a new movie.
- What the hell is this?
- Yeah, it's true story.
It's called High Flying Bird.
It's directed by Steven Soderbergh.
Zazie Beetz is my costar
along with Zachary Quinto.
The movie's about the basketball lockout,
and during the best scene of the movie--
- Oh, man, this is getting crazy.
Jamil Umber and Erick Scott
seem to be going at it in public,
calling each other out on Twitter.
- Never want to make these things public,
but these guys have.
- Yeah.
That's right.
- Did you make it?
- Oh, that's hot.
(group chattering)
- I'm done, I'm canceling my Netflix.
- You mean you're gonna
delete your mom's password.
(group laughs)
- I don't know anyone who
has their own account.
- Oh, you use somebody else's?
- Are you serious?
- I use my mom's.
- Oh my.
(group groans)
- It's Netflix.
- How do we get that code?
(group laughs)
- If your parents seen
what you might also like
and Raquel's got the--
(group laughs)
(energetic music)
- [Announcer] Coming up...
- Billy McFarland just got
sued for three million dollars
and lost.
How do you get it from
Billy if he's in prison?
- Well, somebody in prison
could still have money.
- You know that they don't
take your money to prison
with you, right?
- Well, yeah, I'm well aware of it.
(upbeat music)
- I don't want to waste
time with the wrong guys
and miss out on the one for me.
That's why I'm on eharmony.
- [Eharmony Announcer] At eharmony,
we connect you on what really matters.
That's why every 14 minutes,
someone finds love on eharmony.
Start free today.
- I'm a close talker,
so I was excited about
all-new Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does more.
- Wonderful.
- Sensitivity, strengthens teeth,
it kills germs through my whole mouth.
- I like your confidence.
- Thanks, Mr. Lee.
(bright music)
Now, there's no such thing as too close.
- Yes, there is.
- No, there's not.
- Okay.
- [Luke] All-new Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
- [Olay Narrator] Prestige
creams not living up to the hype?
One jar shatters the competition.
Olay Regenerist hydrates
skin better than creams
costing over 100, 200, and even $400.
Fact check this ad in Good Housekeeping.
Olay.
- Chris Pratt is getting
rid of his dad bod
with fasting and spirituality.
- He's trying real hard
to be unattractive.
Religion and fasting?
Oy.
- We love Hollywood!
We just have a funny way of showing it.
- [Dunkin Narrator] When
Girl Scout ingenuity
meets Dunkin coffee,
you get a cup of can-do.
Girl Scout cookie-inspired
flavors are back at Dunkin.
Try Thin Mints, Coconut Caramel,
or Truffle and Shortbread flavors
and get your $2 medium latte or cappuccino
from two to six PM.
America runs on Dunkin.
- All right, listen up.
Shingles, we've been
protecting this roof for years,
and it's time to go.
- Tell me about it.
I can't hold my water anymore.
Uh oh, I'm going to leak in their bedroom!
- And these blotches and
stains are showing my age.
The homeowner needs to show us some love.
- [Long Roofing Announcer]
Another harsh winter is here.
Better call Long Roofing now
and get a new roof from $99 a month.
(shingle shivers)
♪ We build trust and piece of mind ♪
♪ Into every Long Roofing Roof ♪
- We've been up here for years!
- Come on.
- [Sono Bello Narrator] It's a new year.
It's time for a new you.
This year, get rid of hard-to-lose fat
to reveal the slimmer,
sexier, and more confident you
with Sono Bello,
America's number one
cosmetic surgery specialist.
- I wish that I would have known
about Sono Bello years ago.
I'm 42 and I'm just starting
to live my life the way I want to.
- [Sono Bello Narrator] Using advanced
micro-laser technologies,
Sono Bello can give you
the body you deserve
in as little as one day
with minimal downtime.
Call 888-436-6234
or go to SonoBello.com
for our New Year, New You
limited-time offer.
Find out how to get one area free.
That's your stomach, inner thighs,
even your arms, free.
Get your new body now
with one of our board-certified surgeons.
It's our best offer of the year.
Book now and get one area free.
Payment plans available.
Call 888-436-6234
or go to SonoBello.com.
(remote beeping)
(fire crackling)
- [Cyprus Announcer] Stay warm and cozy
with GasFireplaces.com.
(fire crackling)
Cyprus Air's Presidents Day Sale is here.
Convert your wood-burning fireplace to gas
and get up to 80% off
with installation as early as next week.
Visit your nearest showroom
or schedule a free in-home visit online
at GasFireplaces.com.
- [Pay It Forward Announcer] Every day,
people in our community
are making an impact.
Cutting hair for the homeless,
helping seniors,
keeping kids safe.
They are all paying it forward.
Easterns Automotive
Group wants to recognize
those serving the community.
Go to Fox5DC.com
to nominate those making
a difference today.
(bright music)
(energetic music)
- [Announcer] TMZ online
and on your phone, 24/7.
(upbeat music)
And now, TMZ Piracy presents
X Marks the Spot,
to where disgraced Fyre
Festival Founder Billy McFarland
hopefully has something valuable buried
'cause he's on the hook
for a crap-load of cash.
Yarg!
- So, Billy McFarland is in trouble again.
He just got sued for three
million dollars and lost.
So, this investment company, EHL,
funded him three million dollars
three weeks before the Fyre Festival,
and they never got paid back.
So, they now have sued him
for the three million dollars
plus interest plus legal fees,
and they won.
- [Announcer] Festival co-founder Ja Rule
was mentioned in the suit,
but isn't on the hook for the three mil,
which means they got to
get it all from Billy.
One question, though.
- How do you get it from
Billy if he's in prison?
- Well, somebody in prison
can still have money.
- You know that they don't take your money
to prison with you, right?
- Well, yeah.
- [Announcer] Yes, but
hopefully Billy's money
is protected via the method
any solid financial
planner would recommend.
- Dig a hole in his
backyard and put in a bag.
- It's a pretty good idea.
- It's a terrible idea.
- What about under the
sea like a lobster trap
and then you like bring it
up when you're out of prison.
- [Announcer] Yeah, unless
some lobster swipes it
and is living large on your cheddar, yo.
But here's a better
idea for Billy's money.
- He put it in commissary.
You invest it in commissary.
- Pretty made-up.
I've got 14 billion
dollars in the commissary.
- Yeah, that's a lot of
instant noodles, huh?
(group laughs)
- [Announcer] Well, the point is,
hopefully Billy's got that
three mil buried someplace.
- I know a lot of people
who have money buried.
- You've actually seen people bury money
in their back yard.
- A thousand percent.
- [Announcer] Wow,
that's a lot of percent,
so she must be telling the truth.
Lying conman goodbye, everybody!
(upbeat music)
Coming up.
- Sheila E.
She sends a little message
to her number-one fan.
- Who?
- Eric.
(Harvey gasps)
- I love her.
- Oh my God, Eric.
(group laughs)
(upbeat music)
(bright music)
- Ah, the old crew.
Remember when we all used
to go to the cafeteria
and just chow down midday?
- You mean, like, lunch?
- Come on, voted most likely
to help people save $668
when they switch?
- At this school?
- Didn't you get caught
in the laminating machine?
(Box laughs dryly)
- Box, have a great summer, Danielle.
Ooh, Danielle, control yourself.
I'd like to slow it down
here with a special discount
for a special girl.
Danielle, this one's for you.
- Here's your Buick, sir.
- Actually, that's my Buick.
- Your Buick doesn't have a roof rack.
- This is my Buick.
- How are we gonna fit
in your mom's Buick?
- Easy.
- I like that new Buick.
- Me, too.
- I was actually talking about that Buick.
- I knew that.
- Did you?
- [Buick Announcer]
Buick's fresh new lineup
is full of surprises.
Get great deals on our
expectation-shattering lineup.
Pay no interest for 72
months on most Buick models.
(bright music)
(gentle music)
- [Xfinity Narrator] You.
All of you.
How you live.
What you love.
That's what inspired us
to create America's
most advanced internet,
internet that puts you in charge.
That protects what's important.
And handles everything
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond wifi.
This is x-fi.
Simple, easy, awesome.
Xfinity, the future of awesome.
(remote beeping)
- [Cyprus Announcer] Stay warm and cozy
with GasFireplaces.com.
(flame crackling)
Cyprus Air's Presidents Day Sale is here.
Convert your wood-burning fireplace to gas
and get up to 80% off with installation
as early as next week.
Visit your nearest showroom
or schedule a free in-home visit online
at GasFireplaces.com.
- [Sports Narrator]
College hoops contenders
battle back-to-back in a
big game Saturday on Fox.
- [Game Announcer] For the win, go!
- [Sports Narrator]
First, Charles Matthews
and number five Michigan
look for revenge
in a rematch with 24th-ranked Wisconsin.
Then, Big East scoring
machine Marcus Howard
looks to spark number 10 Marquette
against reigning champs
number 14 Villanova.
- [Sports Commentator] Exclamation point!
- [Sports Narrator] A
big game double-header
tips off Saturday at 11:30 eastern on Fox
and the Fox Sports app.
- [Announcer] Closed captioning
and other consideration
for TMZ provided by:
- [Advil Announcer]
With Advil, you'll ask,
what sore muscles?
What pounding head?
Advil is relief that's fast.
Strength that lasts.
You'll ask, what pain?
With Advil.
- [Dove Announcer] Can
your hair survive damage?
Dove Intensive Repair
Conditioner proves it can.
We treat one brush with Dove conditioner
and expose both to heat styling,
to bleaching, and even coloring.
The difference is clear.
The brush treated with
Dove is visibly smoother
and protected against damage.
(bright music)
Dove Intensive Repair conditioner,
for 100% touchably beautiful hair.
Since once conditioner doesn't fit all,
Dove UltraCare conditioners.
- [Announcer] The TMZ Celebrity Tour
has a new home directly across
from the Hollywood and Highland Center
in the heart of Tinseltown.
On-board this bus, you never
know who you might see.
Kim Kardashian.
Ben Affleck.
The Rock, Mariah Carey.
Justin Bieber.
Kevin Hart.
Get your tickets online
or at the fabulous TMZ
Tour center in Hollywood.
TMZ Celebrity Tour!
(energetic music)
- It's good to see you, Sheila.
- I know it is.
- Sheila E.
Wow, LAX.
- Love Sheila E.
- First thing she said
that Prince's Superbowl's
halftime show, best ever.
- It was the best.
You couldn't beat that.
Couldn't plan it any better.
It rained when he played Purple Rain.
It's the best Superbowl ever.
- Most importantly,
she sent a little message
to her number one fan.
- Who?
- Eric.
(Harvey gasps)
- Hi, Eric at work.
Sheila E., here.
I heard you're a Prince fan.
Are you a Sheila E. Fan?
- [Charlie] He has all your records.
- All right.
- I do.
- The next time I see you,
we get a big hug, all right?
Love you.
- I love her.
- Oh my God, Eric.
- I say, you know, Eric's
not here right now.
We never know if this is
actually gonna happen.
I'll take it on his behalf right now.
Oh yes.
- Don't be jealous.
- How can I like transfer this like hug?
(staff cheering)
How'd it feel?
- Charlie is really good
at transmitting things
from one person to another.
(staff laughs)
(bright music)
- [Charlie] Thank you, Sheila.
Bye.
(intense music)
(bright music)
- I'm a lawyer.
(suspenseful jingle)
(stately jingle)
(bright orchestral overture)