- [Announcer] A UK Channel,
a new season of Midsomer Murders,
then it was North America's first school
for secret agents, Camp X,
followed by an all new Bletchley Circle.
British Television at its best.
(uplifting music)
("Da Butt" by E.U.)
- [Narrator] The '80s.
A time of differing memories.
- The '80s were the time of my life.
- You're just survivin' in this state,
like complete nothingness.
- [Narrator] Divergent music.
- We just did anything and everything.
We were just crazy.
- All right!
- If you can't move to go-go,
you weren't meant to move.
(funky music)
- Come on!
- [Narrator] Development.
- Washington was emerging as the
great cosmopolitan world capital.
- [Narrator] Defending championships.
- From Riggins, good hold!
- I went from being
pretty smart to the next day a buffoon.
- [Narrator] And death.
- We'd have shootings, but
you'd have overdose deaths.
- I personally had a huge
number of friends that I lost.
- [Narrator] And a mayor
who defined the city.
- That little white powder
is so powerful.
- He was the sun around
which we all orbited.
- [Narrator] Join us as
we travel back in time
to Washington in the '80s.
("Da Butt" by E.U.)
("Funkytown" by Lipps Inc.)
- [Narrator] Washington at
the beginning of the '80s,
still rebuilding after the '68 riots.
- I think the residents
were feeling hopeful.
We had a new mayor.
I think there was a good feeling.
We were all just coming off
of the Civil Rights era,
and so the community was
building and coexisting.
- We'd just had home rule for a few years,
and it just sounded like
everything was gonna be great.
Of course, it wasn't.
("The Blue Wrath" by I Monster)
- [Narrator] Washington, D.C.
was still a city divided.
- One black city and one white city.
One city in poverty,
and one city doing well.
- [Narrator] Middle class white flight
meant the 172,000 white
residents who remained
tended to be above average income,
and live in the city's
leafier Northwest suburbs.
- And where the white wards,
that were quote-unquote,
received anything they want,
and there was the other wards,
the forgotten wards, that
were out there hanging out.
- [Narrator] African-Americans,
who made up 70% of the city's residents,
tended to live and work in the poorer
eastern quadrants of the
city, and close to downtown.
♪ This town ♪
♪ It's coming like a ghost town ♪
- When you drove downtown
with your parents,
who made sure the doors were locked.
You know, everything was boarded up,
downtown was a lot of
crime, it was a scary place.
- There was some hope
that that would change,
but there was nothing yet
that gave an indication
that change was really coming.
("Another One Bites the Dust" by Queen)
- [Narrator] The Federal
City's most prominent resident
found himself in a similar
state of stagnation.
- It is a crisis of confidence.
- Four hostages had been taken in Iran,
we had 21% interest rates, 13% inflation.
- Washington was, as it is now,
a predominantly Democratic town,
so Washington wanted this
President to succeed.
- [Narrator] The rest of
America did not feel the same.
- NBC News now makes its projection,
Reagan is our projected winner.
♪ Another one bites the dust ♪
(crowd cheers)
♪ And another one down ♪
- I, Ronald Reagan,
do solemnly swear,
that I will faithfully
execute the office of Presi--
- [Narrator] Two months later,
just as Republican Ronald
Reagan took the Oath of Office,
Ayatollah Khomeini of Iran
released all 52 hostages.
(crowd cheers)
- I am convinced
they suspected that Ronald Reagan
would give them 48 hours,
and if the hostages
weren't on the way home,
there would be military action.
(crowd cheers)
(marching band plays)
- [Narrator] Though Washingtonians
were excited to welcome the hostages,
most didn't the feel the
same about the new President.
- Depressed would be a
good way of describing
the fact that Ronald Reagan
was bringing with him
a whole new political culture.
- [Man] There were fur
coats all over the place.
There was a perception that
the California conservatives
who came were a pretty rich crowd,
and not very much in touch
with the average folks.
("Take On Me" by A-ha)
- I think that the gay
community at that time
had an understandable
amount of trepidation.
You know, what was this
President gonna be like?
- I gave Reagan all the
attention he deserved.
He was not the friend of the city.
- [Narrator] Others were more welcoming.
- From the election, there
were one-word difference
between president and resident,
and he wanted to bridge the gap
between resident and president,
and I believe that, and I appreciate that,
because I'm the mayor of the city,
and he's gonna be one of my constituents.
- I think he knew more about
how Washington functioned
than a lot of other presidents.
He was the only president that I've known
who actually invited the
local media to meet with him.
- When Reagan came to town,
that arts beat and entertainment
beat just exploded,
because Reagan brought all of his
showbiz connections to town.
They had his first inauguration,
they had this huge event.
(Ray Charles sings)
And Reagan set the tone
for movies and show
business in Washington.
(soft jazz music)
- Washington was emerging
as the great cosmopolitan
world capital it is today.
It was a great time in America
and it was a great time
for the Reaganauts.
- [Narrator] Until March 30th, 1981.
(crowd chattering)
(gunshots popping)
(clattering)
(woman shrieking)
(background murmuring)
As Reagan was leaving
the Washington Hilton,
John Hinckley, Jr. fired six times.
(men shouting)
- Get up!
One shot hit press secretary James Brady
critically wounding him.
Another ricocheted off
the presidential limousine
lodging in Reagan's lung.
- [Reporter] What are you
gonna do when you get home?
- Sit down. (laughing)
("Take On Me" by A-ha)
(crowd cheering)
- [Narrator] Within a month,
Reagan was back at work.
("Take On Me" by A-ha)
And the Washington Hilton had a nickname.
- Meet me over there by the Hilton.
Oh, the Hinckley Hilton.
- The Hinckley Hilton.
I don't think I've ever
driven by that hotel
without thinking about it.
- [Narrator] Back at his desk,
the president worked
with his administration
to fulfill his campaign
promise to cut spending.
Growing discontent with
existing treatments
prompted cuts in mental health services.
- You began to see large
numbers of panhandlers
appearing on the streets of Washington.
(man laughs)
(soft music)
- Bein' D.C. where the president reside,
he was thinkin' we shouldn't
have some places like this.
(birds squawking)
- I walk the streets, and I
sleep on the goddamn streets.
(soft music)
- [Narrator] Many district
homeless were veterans
damaged by their experiences in Vietnam,
fighting an unpopular war.
♪ I want to know what love is ♪
(crowd applauding)
♪ I want you to show me ♪
(crowd cheering)
- Didn't even have to go.
I wanted to go.
Everything I put my heart into,
you come back and you got dumped now.
♪ Now you can show me ♪
- [Narrator] In 1980, Congress
authorized construction
of a Vietnam memorial on the Mall.
Following a nationwide competition,
the design for a sunken
reflective black granite wall
by Maya Lin, a 21-year-old
college student, was selected.
- It was so simple and so
direct that it was incredible.
- [Narrator] But not everyone
was happy with the design.
- I said this doesn't look
like something honoring
these people's service
and there was a tremendous
cultural artistic debate
that went on in this town
and a lot of people felt
are they dishonoring
the vets by doing this?
- [Narrator] Eventually the design
for the memorial was amended
and three soldiers were added,
but on its opening in 1982,
the strength of the original
design became evident.
- I'm here to pay eulogy and
homage to all of my comrades
didn't make it back with me.
- I think they wanted
something more heroic
but I think they got something
that was even more profound.
- I think what turned it
around was not the black walls,
it's the names on the walls.
And I will say it turned out from
the way that thing's been received
that I was wrong on that one.
Wrong, big time.
- And I love the American
people for being here
and just saying thank you,
because that's all we
want, is to hear that.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] For more than a century,
the city had supported
two nationally recognized
daily newspapers,
the more progressive Washington Post
and more conservative Washington Star.
But the recession and shrinking
demand for evening dailies
forced the Star into bankruptcy in 1981.
- TV killed 'em.
People who watch the TV news go home,
they don't sit there and read their paper.
Click. (background chattering)
- For about a year and a half,
we were a one-paper town,
and that was, I felt,
a little dangerous.
- [Narrator] But in a
sign of the growing clout
of conservative voices, an upstart daily
with an unwavering point of view
hit the newsstands in 1982.
- [Reporter] It's called
The Washington Times
and it's owned by the publishing arm
of the Reverend Moon's Unification church.
- I wasn't excited to see the
moonie paper come around, no.
Reverend Moon was a great
Christian evangelist from Korea.
He obviously felt that
it would be nice to have
a good mouthpiece in Washington.
- My column used to appear
in The Washington Times
on a regular, you know, twice a week,
and every conservative read it.
I mean, it was something we
had that we'd never had before.
(upbeat music)
(motor humming)
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] No one who
worked the newsrooms
of Washington of the '80s can
forget January 13th, 1982.
- I had just come across the
bridge in a blinding snowstorm
and when I got 10 feet off
the bridge we heard a crunch.
- [Narrator] At 4:01 p.m.,
Air Florida Flight 90
crashed into the 14th Street bridge.
(propellers whirring)
- We get down there and we
don't really have a method
for dealing with that
kind of mass casualty.
The radio systems didn't
function like they should,
we didn't have any place
to deal with the bodies.
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] Passerby Lenny
Skutnik dove into the water
to help save a drowning woman.
- [Reporter] We have just learned
that that woman fighting to
survive in the icy Potomac
was one of the stewardesses
on board the plane,
her name Kelly Dunman.
- He really symbolized I
think for a lot of people here
that people wanted to help
and were willing to help each other.
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] 74 people on the plane
and four on the bridge were killed.
- One of my dearest
friends was on that plane.
She was the mother of
three young children.
I miss her to this day.
(sirens wailing)
- [Narrator] As word of the crash spread
and the Washington Press
corps descended on the scene,
it became clear that another
tragedy had struck the region.
- Reporters couldn't get there
because the Metro train also had derailed.
- [Narrator] 30 minutes
after the plane crash
an Orange Line train jumped
the tracks in a tunnel,
near Federal Triangle.
- [Reporter] Two women and a man
whose names have not been
released were killed.
- That forced the region
to think oh my goodness,
what do we do if?
- So for some many of our--
- [Narrator] By 1982,
Barry's first term as mayor
was coming to a close.
For the first time since
his election in 1978,
voters were given the
chance to judge his record.
(funky, upbeat music)
- He was elected by whites.
As he won essentially
with the votes of people
(people singing)
in wards one, three, two, and six.
- And this is just the beginning
of what we're going to do here.
- [Narrator] But once in power,
Barry knew that tying his political future
to the city's white
residents was unsustainable.
- He made an incredibly
prudent political decision
to switch his base to black,
through minority contracting programs
and bringing black folks
into key positions in the government.
- I can remember him saying, "Listen.
"You're gonna be able to advance,
"you got to get prepared for leadership,"
and for somebody like me,
I got to be chief because of Barry.
- [Narrator] Barry used
the power of his position
to encourage the creation and development
of African American owned businesses.
♪ We found the proper place ♪
- And if you're gonna do business in D.C.,
one of the first questions they'd ask you,
do you have minority
participation in this deal?
What came about was a philosophy that
white business should partner up
with qualified African
American business people
and once you get a black city council
all of a sudden the white
law firms start saying
we're gonna have black partners,
and some of the white
businesses start saying
we have to have black lobbyists.
- [Narrator] The increased flow of money
moving through the city's economy
swelled the district's coffers,
giving Barry the income
to spend on projects
that benefited the city's poorer youth
and build a base for the
rest of his political career.
- My most memorable program
is the summer job program.
Over a hundred thousand young people
went through our summer job program.
- I was just at some event
and the guy who was in charge
of the people parking the cars
came up to me, he says,
"I got my first job
"in the Marion Barry summer job program."
He said, "Now I help to run this company."
- That was the bomb.
You go down 500 C Street and
there's a long line of kids
waitin' in line to get
their checks, you know.
You would see them all downtown
at The Go-Go at night. (laughing)
So, that was awesome, yes indeed.
- [Narrator] Recognizing
that the district's aging
were underserved, Barry
also invested heavily
in services for the elderly.
- And the flip side of that for Barry was
in addition to that being a good thing,
was that he would take
buses, recreation buses,
and take them all down to vote.
(crowd chanting)
- [Narrator] In 1982,
Barry was elected to a
second term as mayor,
with 81% of the vote.
- I want to thank all
of you for reaffirming
your faith in me.
(audience cheering)
- It was clear that his
success in the election
had been largely through black folks
and not from the white community.
He said get over it.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] During his first term,
Barry had honored promises
made to the gay community,
a core constituency that
helped to elect him.
- [Man] He understood that
we were a political power.
- Just his willingness to say I will have
openly gay people in my administration.
Nobody did that at that
time, so that was huge.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Barry's actions
helped to establish D.C.
as one of the country's
most gay-friendly cities.
- It affected most gay
people's social lives
in that they became more open.
- [Woman] It gave the
community this enormous number
of healthy, happy ways of meeting people
and so it made it a lot
easier for people to come out.
("L'Amour" by Erasure)
- [Narrator] By 1984,
expansion of D.C.'s annual gay pride day
to a week-long festival was complete,
cementing Washington's status
as home to one of the country's largest
and most vibrant gay communities.
(background cheering)
Improvement in the city's fortunes
also spread to the football field.
("Thriller" by Michael Jackson)
In 1981, team owner Jack Kent
Cooke fired coach Jack Pardee
and replaced him
with San Diego offensive
coordinator, Joe Gibbs.
- At first I said if I'm not successful
hey, that's part of life,
but when I got there what I realized
is just how many people depend on you.
- [Narrator] The team
began the season 0-5.
- I thought I was gonna be first guy
to ever coach in the NFL
and never win a game,
tell Pat please sell the dog,
I'd hate to come home and see that fella
draped over the steps. (laughing)
- [Narrator] But a third of
the way through the '81 season,
wins replaced losses, and
the team finished 8-8.
- They had a really unique squad.
Theismann was just really slick.
- Hit.
- Joe T. was probably
one of the most passionate
football players,
I mean that guy wanted to be successful.
(crowd cheering)
- [Man] Riggins was a bull.
I mean you had Joe Washington
who was just this small, speedy guy.
Art Monk, anything you
threw up, he caught.
- Their hearts were big and fat,
and they put a lot of
meat against that line.
- [Crowd] We want Grant!
We want Grant!
- [Narrator] After going 8-1
and first in the NFC East
in the strike-shortened 1982 season,
they hosted the NFC championship game
against their fiercest rival.
- The excitement at RFK you
heard outside the stadium,
just up in the neighborhood
you'd just hear that roaring crowd.
(crowd cheering)
- [Narrator] The home
team was leading 24-17
with less than seven minutes remaining.
- [Announcer] Play action fake to Dorsett,
screen path, batted in the air by Lanley.
Darryl Grant's there picks it off.
Touchdown, Washington Redskins.
Unbelievable!
- [Man] The stadium was rocked.
It was thunderous.
- [Announcer] I do not believe it!
(crowd roaring)
- [Narrator] With that win,
the team headed to Pasadena
to play the Miami Dolphins
in Superbowl XVII.
(football players chanting)
The game was close throughout.
- It came down to the 4th quarter,
I think we were on the plus 41 yard line,
and it was 4th and one, and
I made a call to go for it.
- [Announcer] There goes
(drowned out by music).
Their touchdown surprised them.
Hand to Riggins.
He's got a good hold, he's
got the first down for 40.
He's gone!
The 35, the 30, the 20, he's gone!
Touchdown, Washington Redskins.
Holy cow, was that a play or what!
(crowd cheering)
- [Narrator] The final
score, 27-17, Washington.
- Redskins are number one!
- Everybody poured into the streets
of M Street in Georgetown.
It was euphoric.
The city's team finally
brought home the bacon.
(woman shrieking)
♪ Pump pump pump pump me up ♪
(funky music)
- [Narrator] Football
wasn't the only thing
making fans at RFK cheer.
- The Back To School Boogie,
the battle of the bands,
you'd get an opportunity
to see all these go-go bands perform
inside of a huge stadium.
♪ Come out here with family ♪
- And I used to always say
if you can't move to go-go,
you weren't meant to move.
- I remember first time
hearing Trouble Funk,
there's a song, Pump Me Up.
♪ Pump pump pump pump me up ♪
♪ Like the man with the super S ♪
And Henry Rollins, he was my best friend,
we heard it on the radio
and we just pulled the car
over to listen to the song.
♪ From the East to West ♪
- [Narrator] In addition to
Chuck Brown and Trouble Funk,
bands such as Rare Essence and E.U.
created a music and culture
proud of its D.C. roots.
- Look what I brought to y'all, all right?
- Go-go was a product of a time
when D.C. public schools
had more music programs.
- Kids couldn't afford to buy instruments
and so the kids would
check out their instruments
and they'd go home to practice all right,
but with the local go-go band.
- [Narrator] Live recordings,
better known as PA tapes,
became a form of currency for go-go fans.
- We used to go to the go-gos
with our big boom boxes
and stand in front of the speakers.
- It was and still is a big thing
to get your name called out,
especially if your name is
always heard on the PA tapes, you know.
- Woo, that was a big feeling
and so you wanted that
PA tape from this date.
(funky music)
- [Narrator] The City's
insatiable appetite for live go-go
led to performances
springing up all over town.
(funky music)
- Everybody represented
where they came from.
Junk Yard from Barry Farm,
Pat Worth named himself after the area.
- My first ever experience
playing live with a go-go band
was in my friend's backyard
and people would crowd
around and listen to us.
- [Narrator] A compulsion
to play live music
that lead to an unlikely
sharing of stages.
- A lot of the regular
clubs like The Bayou
and Desperados only booked big rock bands
or big-named people, so
we would play anywhere
and it would end up that
we would play together.
("Should I Stay or Should
I Go" by The Clash)
- [Narrator] One of these crossover venues
was at 930 F Street, Northwest.
- Their slogan was a place and a time.
- [Narrator] When original owners
Dody DiSanto and Jon Bowers
opened The 930 Club in 1980,
their choice of location
in the heart of downtown
was unconventional.
- [Man] When the 930 was
there, there were peep shows
and you know, liquor
stores and strip joints.
People couldn't afford to
buy expensive real estate
so they had to do it in
the bad parts of town.
- [Narrator] The tiny odd-shaped space
was an acquired taste.
- There was really not
much room for the audience.
It was like you were in a lobby.
We would have bands show up
who were appalled and ask--
♪ Should I stay or should I go ♪
So where's the club?
And some bands walked out.
DJ Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh
Prince, Will Smith, walked out,
two sold-out shows.
(rock music)
Course when the band did go on,
you were right in front of them.
(rock music)
There was no closer
experience to see a show
than the old 930 club.
(rock music)
- [Narrator] A unique venue
that became a favorite
of the local hardcore punk scene,
defined by its inclusion of anyone
who didn't feel they belonged.
- If you grew up in this town
I think you feel really marginalized
from one reason or another.
- [Narrator] D.C. punk
gave birth to bands like
Government Issue, State of Alert,
and Minor Threat with Ian
MacKaye on lead vocals.
(punk rock singing)
- We identify as Washington D.C.
It was a chip on our shoulder.
- [Narrator] The region also produced
the groundbreaking Bad Brains.
(punk rock singing)
- Bad Brains were four guys
from Anacostia in PG County
and they were just an incredible band.
(punk rock music)
- Yeah!
♪ They're playing basketball ♪
♪ We love that basket ♪
[Narrator] The early '80s saw an explosion
of the popularity of Georgetown
University basketball.
♪ Playing basketball ♪
- I can remember when Georgetown was just
a type of ivy league Jesuit school
but then John Thompson
came and turned it around
and everyone was Hoyas, Hoyas, Hoyas.
♪ Playing basketball ♪
- [Narrator] The team's
tough defense-minded style
helped to attract a
strong, loyal following.
- A predominantly black basketball team
at a really good university,
that inspired a lot of us.
We hung out in Georgetown,
we wore Georgetown University sweatshirts.
- It was like a party to me.
It was the place to be, I mean. (laughing)
The energy was all over the place.
- [Narrator] In March of 1982, the Hoyas
led by center Patrick Ewing
advanced to the NCAA championship game.
With less than 10 seconds left
they had a chance to
take the winning shot.
- [Announcer] Fred Brown with the ball,
oh, throws it to the wrong guy.
- [Man] I had to turn the TV off.
I couldn't stand to watch anymore.
- [Narrator] Two seasons later,
the team went 34-3,
winning the big east championship.
(crowd cheering)
♪ They're playing basketball ♪
- [Narrator] They advanced
through the NCAA regional,
the final four, to the
championship game against Houston.
(ball clinks)
♪ Basketball ♪
- Michael Graham just goes
up and tomahawk dunks it,
and he looks at Pat and
he just points at him
just to let him know okay, we got this.
(crowd cheering)
- [Announcer] Georgetown wins the title,
and Fred Brown gets the hug.
♪ To the, to the hoop ♪
- [Narrator] The Hoyas were
welcomed back to Washington as champions,
and Coach Thompson as a hero.
- And I think all of us feel
a great pride in what you've accomplished.
("How Soon Is Now" by The Smiths)
- [Narrator] As President
Reagan campaigned
for reelection in 1984, Mitch Snyder,
the leader of homeless advocacy group,
Community For Creative
Non-Violence, or CCNV,
staged a hunger strike to demand
the administration renovate a shelter
in an abandoned federal building.
- The administration's
saying in everybody's name,
including ours, that it
has no responsibility
to people who are the poorest of the poor.
("How Soon Is Now" by The Smiths)
- My sister-in-law, for a very brief time,
was in HUD dealing with the homeless
and she wanted to go and
interview Mitch Snyder
and essentially the
administration said don't do it,
and don't do anything.
♪ Needs to be loved, just
like everybody else does ♪
- [Narrator] 51 days into his
protest, Snyder got his wish.
- I think we capitulated to some degree.
Truth be told, Reagan's a sensitive,
I mean something like
that would affect him.
- [Narrator] Two days later,
President Ronald Reagan was reelected.
- You ain't seen nothin' yet.
(audience applauding)
- I had several friends
that seemed to have
this continual flu bug,
and then it became pneumonia
and then they just died.
- [Narrator] As Reagan
began his second term,
a lack of action towards
those suffering and dying
from HIV infection persisted.
- [Reporter] White House officials confirm
that the president has never talked
with his surgeon general about AIDS.
- [Narrator] Those in
the district turned to
The Washington Blade for information.
- The community desperately needed
information about the disease.
- [Narrator] On April 4th, 1983,
the Whitman-Walker Clinic held D.C.'s
first public forum on the epidemic.
- Whitman Walker was one
of the founding fathers
of AIDS information.
But they also helped house people,
they helped to feed people.
They had to actually step
in and become involved
in the link between the doctors
and the hospitals and the patients
because a lot of people were being
turned away from hospitals.
♪ Can you tell me why ♪
- [Narrator] But the deaths
of two public figures
with ties to Washington
forced the country,
and the president, to act.
- Rock Hudson was familiar
with the president himself
and an individual who had one, particular,
very influential friend in Washington.
Elizabeth Taylor.
Not only was she an icon of the movies,
she was also married to a
US senator from Virginia,
John Warner.
And so minds were changed and
the perception began to shift.
- That science will continue
to find the critical answers.
- Jerry Smith, my favorite tight end
for the Washington Redskins,
then he was stricken with AIDS,
it became apparent that
this He-Man was gay.
- [Darian] Ronald Reagan's
opinion definitely changed
because these were your friends dying.
Same thing happened to me.
- [Crowd] Gay rights now!
Gay rights now!
- [Narrator] A year after
Jerry Smith's passing,
an estimated half million
people descended on Washington
with a second march for
gay and lesbian rights.
♪ Every bond you break ♪
♪ Every step you take
I'll be watching you ♪
- [Narrator] The highlight,
a massive memorial quilt
covering the Mall with the names of the
thousands of Americans
who had died of AIDS.
♪ I'll be watching you ♪
- America is a quilt,
made up of many patches,
many pieces, many textures
where everybody fits.
- Everyone who was there
just looked at each other
and either cried or smiled
or a combination of the two.
♪ I'll be watching you ♪
♪ Every move you make ♪
♪ Every vow you break ♪
♪ Every smile you fake ♪
("Road To Nowhere" by Talking Heads)
- [Narrator] By 1987, the
decade's early promise
was beginning to fade.
♪ We're on a road to nowhere ♪
♪ Come on inside ♪
- [Narrator] Attempts to give the district
congressional representation
and statehood had gone nowhere.
Many started to ask if
Barry's management of the city
was part of the problem.
- Marion Barry was
already starting to have
some budget problems,
running some deficits,
but he didn't cut his crony contracts,
he didn't cut waste fraud and abuse,
what he cut was 1,500 police officers.
- [Narrator] Mayor Barry's
lifestyle also raised questions.
- [Reporter] Karen Johnson
just told authorities
that she sold the mayor
cocaine, 20 to 30 times,
from late 1980 to 1982.
- [Man] He was notorious
for staying out late
with women who were not his wife.
This is when he would
use the security detail
to procure women for him.
- Marion Barry tonight angrily denied
that he has been hospitalized
after overdosing on cocaine.
- Marion Barry became too
comfortable with power.
After winning over the
overwhelming majority
of the African American population,
he felt he could no longer be removed.
- He was powerful,
he could make a lot of
things happen in your ward.
Hey, do you want that new fire station?
Do you want the library?
- [Narrator] Growing
discontent that led Barry
to have real competition in
the '86 mayoral election.
- In Washington D.C., where
the voter registration
was 10 to one, Democrats to Republicans,
I got a third of the vote.
- [Narrator] Though Schwartz's tally
exceeded everyone's expectations,
Barry's base delivered him a third term,
with 61% of the vote.
- Washington Post endorsed
him three straight times,
I think with growing reluctance
or something like that
the third time.
(background chattering)
- [Narrator] But the
electorate and opinion pages
cooling on Barry did nothing
to slow his larger than life persona.
- When people elected me,
they didn't elect me pope.
They elected me mayor.
I'd go out at night at nine
o'clock or ten o'clock,
what did that have to do with anything?
♪ And the beat goes on ♪
- Because of his short attention span
and he could compartmentalize,
he would go out at night
with the famous, "I'm a night owl,"
as if that would wash things away.
- [Narrator] The city paper
dubbed him Mayor For Life.
- When you're for the
people, the people know it.
He's the only one I seen
that stood there for us.
- [Narrator] If he hadn't been mayor,
Barry's nightlife would
not have been surprising
as D.C.'s bar and club scene
reached a peak in the mid-80s.
- There was this club called The Foxtrappe
and it was the place
to go for the buppies.
- That was the quintessential place
where high-income sophisticated people go.
(upbeat music)
- You dress up to go there,
you dressed up your behavior too
and your manners,
(chuckling) in most cases.
- [Narrator] Because the
Foxtrappe wasn't just a nightclub,
it was a D.C. institution
where members of the
black congressional caucus
rubbed shoulders with African
American business leaders
and celebrities.
♪ Tam bo li de say de moi ya ♪
♪ Yeah, Jambo Jambo ♪
♪ Way to party oh we goin' ♪
♪ Oh, jambali ♪
- There was always an
interesting event going on.
A lot of them were fundraisers.
A lot of them were what we
would call networking events,
and it was very important for
young, black professionals
to feel a sense of solidarity
and to share their experiences.
It was a great way to socialize
and also to meet new people.
- It was nice but, you know,
it was an important step in the process.
("All Night Long" by Lionel Ritchie)
- [Narrator] D.C. super discos
were also experiencing
unparalleled popularity.
- The Pier, the Lost and
Found, the Other Side,
it was a blast, a freakin' hoot.
Insane.
Redskins came in their Redskins jerseys.
You'd run into extremely famous people
and they all merged together.
♪ Oh, jamabli ♪
- [Narrator] A vibrant party
scene that became synonymous
with the '80s recreational drug of choice.
(upbeat music)
- Everyone did cocaine.
It was everywhere, and it was considered
to be like a cocktail.
You had a glass of gin,
you had a line of coke.
- [Narrator] But as participation
was reliant on a certain lifestyle
it was something many average
Americans never experienced.
- It was a subculture that I
knew absolutely nothing about
and it was brought to the forefront.
- [Narrator] In 1984, sophomore Len Bias
from Prince George's County
led the University of Maryland
to the Atlantic Coast Conference title
bringing national attention to the team.
(thrilling music)
(crowd cheering)
Len Bias's senior season
was highlighted by a win
over the top-ranked Tar Heels.
(crowd cheering)
- [Announcer] Maryland has
knocked off North Carolina
in one of the biggest upsets this year
and there is one happy Len Bias.
- You couldn't stop him.
He had the athleticism,
he had the defense,
he can rebound.
- [Narrator] Skills that
made him the second,
overall pick in the 1986 NBA draft.
- We were just so happy
and it was just a
wonderful, wonderful time.
He comes back to Maryland
and I'm not at home,
and I never see him again.
♪ Tell all your friends
they can go my way ♪
♪ Pay your toll, sell your soul ♪
- Investigators this morning
are trying to determine
exactly what caused
the death Thursday of former
University of Maryland
basketball star, Len Bias.
(radio chattering)
- [Narrator] The autopsy showed
that Bias had died from
a cocaine overdose.
- Like I said, there was a subculture
that I knew nothing
about until my son died
and then boom, you find
out this is real life.
- I love you Leonard and I'll miss you.
I'll see you in heaven one day.
("White Lines" by Grandmaster Melle Mel)
- [Narrator] As cocaine use was
peaking in the Washington region,
a new, more potent,
smuggleable form of the drug
began to appear.
- The first time that we
made a seizure of crack
was up in Northwest
and from then on it was on.
♪ Ah yeah ♪
- It seemed like suddenly, one day,
we woke up and we were in the middle
of a crack cocaine epidemic and this time
it was the crews of kids who
had grown up with my own kids
who were on the corner
selling crack cocaine
battling over turf.
♪ France a skinny man died of a ♪
- One minute it felt like
we were putting quarters
into the Space Invaders
machine to being a drug dealer.
You had to survive so you join a gang
just to avoid being suppressed by a gang.
- [Narrator] While young
African American men
both profited and died
during the crack epidemic,
some of its most tragic
victims were young women.
- And I was much younger
which I fancied myself a photographer
and I had taken photos of
young women in my neighborhood
when they were seven, eight years old,
the light in their eyes,
the smiles of their faces,
and to see those same young
women prostituting herself
on a corner in her own neighborhood
where everybody knew her
to buy crack cocaine.
- [Narrator] Through it all,
the city and police
departments seemed powerless.
- The Clean Sweep operation was designed
to attack the crowds that were gathering
to buy and sell drugs,
and we just arrested
people in the hundreds.
♪ Rocket ship explodes ♪
♪ And everybody still wants to fly ♪
(radio chattering)
- I was one of the ones that
they grabbed and threw down
and they didn't take me
straight to the precinct.
They had to take me to
D.C. General Hospital first
because I was beaten up pretty badly.
- There wasn't any study to
say does this make sense?
Is there any longterm impact?
The courts were saying we
can't process 700 people.
We'd come in, make the arrest,
in two weeks they're back,
and they're doing the same thing.
- [Officer] I got his chin.
- It ain't mine.
(slow hip-hop music)
♪ Time ♪
(logo whirring)
- [Narrator] While the headlines
were dominated by bad news,
the popularity and profitability
of local TV and radio
made it an exciting time for the business.
- [Announcer] With Paul Berry.
- It was the grand age of competition
between local television stations
and local radio stations.
You could experiment, people
were a little less safe.
- [Narrator] Earlier in the decade,
iconic radio station, D.C. 101
pushed the experimental
envelope to its limits,
hiring a young DJ named Howard Stern
to host its morning show.
- Everybody would come in that day
and say did you hear what Howard Stern did
or said this morning?
- Does she douche with--
- One time when his
wife had a miscarriage,
he did an entire show on it.
- If somebody doesn't want
to listen to my radio program
they should turn the dial and
listen to some other jerk.
- [Narrator] While Howard Stern
was the most shocking DJ in town,
Donnie Simpson was undisputed favorite.
- Every radio station wanted to
figure out a way to attract
young whites and young blacks
and Donnie started mixing
those two kinds of music
that Donnie would say, I'm
playing a fudge ripple.
(laughs)
♪ We all know ♪
♪ That people are the
same wherever you go ♪
- Donnie had the smile, he had the laugh,
he had the bubbly eyes.
- [Man] Great man, thanks.
- [Narrator] Good looks and a personality
made for a new national TV network.
- Today, on video soul.
- When we put Donnie on BET
as the host of Video Soul--
- I'm Donnie Simpson,
can you join me tonight for Video Soul?
That's tonight, Video Soul,
9:00 p.m. Eastern Time,
right here on BET.
- He became instantly,
overnight, a celebrity
and BET began to be defined
by Donnie Simpson and Video Soul.
- We'll be back, we got a second hour--
- It was national and it so it allowed us
to broaden our scope on
who we were as a culture.
(upbeat rock music)
- [Narrator] While cable
TV was in its infancy,
Washington's local affiliates
were at their height.
- Hey, you want depth?
Watch channel 26. (laughing)
This is channel 4, we have fun here.
♪ So good to turn to ♪
- [Announcer] Channel 5,
Washington's most watched station.
- [Broadcaster] From
WJLA TV, Washington's--
- [Narrator] As ratings for local news
created advertising dollars,
battle between sports departments
became particularly fierce.
- It turned into a golden
time of competition
between channel 9 and channel 4.
George Michael had an open checkbook,
George could cover anything he wanted.
Glenn Brenner on the other hand,
was probably the most talented, creative,
hilarious character who ever
worked in television news.
- How are you doing, I
mean, what's the chalk?
- You got an over large--
- Weenie?
- Weenie on the street, sir.
- My weenie's too big?
- George and Glenn hated each other.
They would go to the
Superbowl, get the room number
that the other guy was in
and then walk into the bar and
say hey, drinks on the house!
- [Narrator] Most residents also remember
a favorite news station.
- My favorite was Channel 4.
Jim Vance was just cool.
He's just a smooth cat.
He had a way of telling his stories
without giving up the cool.
- Channel 9 was held in a high regard
as the number one news
station to a lot of people
because they covered the news stories
without opinions raised in them.
(thrilling music)
- Starting with his third term,
there seemed to be a deterioration
in the attention that Marion
Barry paid to the city.
- [Narrator] In January 1987,
the city was shut down
by a massive snowstorm.
- [Darian] Everything stopped.
I had actually hosted a
large party the night before
and we came stumbling out the
door into six feet of snow.
- [Narrator] The day before,
Barry left town to attend
the Superbowl in California.
- It's no good, the guy,
he don't clean the street.
- [Narrator] While the
mayor was in California,
the region was hit with a bigger blizzard
but Barry stuck to his plans,
reportedly partying so hard
he was taken to the hospital.
Barry returned to D.C. the next day.
- It's unfortunate that so much snow fell,
which we certainly aren't responsible for.
(background chanting)
- [Narrator] Barry's lack of attention
was especially problematic,
as crack-related violence
threatened to overrun the city.
- The strange thing about it,
he never would tell you to do anything
except lock up the drug dealers.
- Outside of the killings,
one of the lowest crime
rates in the country.
- [Narrator] At the same time
the district's youth were
dragged into the epidemic,
the city cut funding for
recreational services,
leaving go-gos one of the few
places to meet and gather.
- One element of go-go
is call and response.
It's very easy for a lead talker
to ask a crowd is Southeast
better than Northeast,
and so there's this automatic tribalism.
A few go-go bands would
sort of advertise PCP.
Tell me now, what y'all smoke?
And the people would respond Love Boat.
- And you get a whole bunch
of kids together just to dance
and all that and somebody pulls out a gun.
- [Narrator] Go-go's rise
to national prominence
stalled as the music became
identified with violence.
- It was part of society.
Unfortunately, knuckleheads
like music too.
♪ I'm feeling like a bum now ♪
- [Narrator] Under the
name The Go Go Posse,
a number of local bands recorded a single
promoting an end to the violence,
called D.C. Don't Stand for Dodge City.
♪ Like the wild wild
west and its calamity ♪
♪ But D.C. don't mean Dodge City ♪
♪ D.C. don't mean Dodge City ♪
- Didn't change my life
because go-go music
oftentimes, it would
glorify all of the things
that this particular song
was speaking against.
- [Narrator] As the death toll mounted,
the city gained a dubious title.
- Washington is now called
the murder capital of the country.
(sirens wailing)
- My kids were in high school at the time
and they had on their wall
a list of the people who they knew,
either from their neighborhood
or their school who had died.
Before they graduated
from Dunbar High School,
that list had grown to 25 people.
- [Narrator] While crack created squalor
in previously vibrant
residential neighborhoods,
the city's commercial areas
were enjoying a relative boom.
- Downtown was dead.
And Barry said we gotta
do something about this.
Developers went to him
and said we want this,
we want that, and gave them
the land virtually free
and these projects were built.
- And we persuaded the banks and others
to lend money to these developers.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] After some politicking,
the Georgetown Waterfront
was one of the first
vistas to see results.
- Marion Barry recognized
that Washington Harbor could
be an enormous boom to the city
and so he was very instrumental.
- [Narrator] The success
of projects in Georgetown
and downtown gave Barry the confidence
to try to redevelop less likely locations
including ground zero of the '68 riots.
- If you told someone you were going to 14
they knew you were going
to buy drugs, period.
- [Narrator] The Frank D.
Reeves Municipal Center,
named after the lawyer and
local civil rights leader,
opened in 1986.
- People who were going to
work in those offices every day
would need services,
and even though at the time
it seemed fairly farfetched
there was a certain sense
that it would restore
an element of validity to a
once flourishing neighborhood.
(upbeat music)
- [Narrator] Several
long-closed icons of the past
were also resurrected.
The Old Post Office,
a Romanesque Revival
structure dating to 1899,
had been on the verge of
the wrecking ball for years.
- [Arthur] Sir David Wills,
who was heir to the
tobacco fortune in England,
cast a replica of the Westminster bells
as a bicentennial gift
to the United States.
He had this idea that they should hang
in the dome of the Capitol.
- [Narrator] But the Capitol
wasn't built for that purpose.
- One bong of these great bells
and the Capitol dome would be
sitting down over the Mall.
The congress was so concerned about it
that they appropriated
a new amount of money
and that was what finally
saved the entire building.
- All this was done with partnerships
and I think the results have been amazing.
- [Narrator] Saving Union Station,
a neglected Beaux-Art's masterpiece
that had become the city's
unofficial homeless shelter
became the responsibility of
a public private partnership.
- I thought it was very successful.
They were very careful in
preserving great spaces.
("Axel F" by Harold Faltermeyer)
(background chattering)
(dramatic music)
- [Narrator] D.C.'s downtown areas
received an additional boost
as a slew of local theaters
opened their doors.
- These little companies
started springing up
because downtown was so empty
that they could get space cheap.
The Wooly Mammoth and the Studio theaters
opened on 14th Street,
14th Street sort of became
the center of alternative theater.
- [Narrator] But at first,
residents weren't convinced.
- I would go over there to
watch some of their shows.
10, 15, 20 people in the
audience plus the actors.
- [Narrator] But in
time, people's reluctance
to come downtown eased,
and Washington began its rise
to America's second city of theater.
- Washington was like that.
I mean, it had certain kinds
of cultural niches if you will.
- I'm a Washingtonian and
the first theater I ever saw
was from the top balcony of the National.
- [Narrator] As Washington's
theater scene gained
countrywide attention,
it established an award named in honor
of one of the city's
most acclaimed daughters
to recognize local theatrical excellence.
- The great Washington
Post critic, Richard Coe
called on his friendship with Helen Hayes
and together they created
the Helen Hayes Awards
and once the Helen Hayes Awards started,
more companies started popping up.
By the end of the decade,
Washington was on the
same playing field as Chicago.
- [Narrator] The region's
growing interest in the arts
was exploited by
Washington's TV affiliates,
still hungry for novel programming.
- The critics really-- (drowned
out by orchestral music)
- The king of the critics
in Washington D.C.
was Davey Marlin-Jones.
Davey was one of the
most interesting people
I had ever met.
- There may be something there.
- Davey wore hats.
He also pushed the
envelope with his clothes,
he pushed his envelope in every way.
- Tight.
Taut.
Tense.
- Davey owned this town.
- Inside the theater called life.
- [Narrator] A popular format
that encouraged imitation.
- Every station in town had a critic
and it was because we were all
trying to compete with Davey.
It was one of the great
gags of local television.
When he finished his report,
you didn't know if he liked
the movie or not. (chuckling)
- Hope you find one cinematic
sparkler among them.
Davey Marlin-Jones.
- I tried to make myself
different from Davey
so I used a ratings system.
On my scale of one to four stars,
Raiders of the Lost Ark gets a five.
So at least when I was finished
you would know what I
thought of the movie or not.
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
- [Narrator] In 1986,
Washington's football team
picked up journeyman
quarterback Doug Williams
to back up its young
phenom, Jay Schroeder.
("Walk This Way" by RUN-DMC)
During the following season,
William shared quarterback duties
with the oft-injured Schroeder.
(players shouting)
But once the team made it to the playoffs,
Williams' performance put
an end to any controversy.
- We had to go to Chicago
playing 13 below temperatures.
We won.
("Walk This Way" by RUN-DMC)
The championship game against
the Minnesota Vikings,
I came off the bench and we won the game
and at coach's press conference,
he mentioned that I was gonna
be the starting quarterback,
me being the first African American
to play in the Superbowl.
I really cherished that time,
and for two weeks leading up to that game
it was pretty much crazy.
- [Narrator] The game started out badly.
- [Announcer] Touchdown, Denver, 56--
- The score was 10 to nothing
against the Redskins in the first quarter.
- [Narrator] And then, it got worse.
- I hyper-extended my knee,
didn't know it at that particular time
whether or not I was gonna be able
to finish the football game.
- I was gonna substitute
for him, he said hey,
get back out, I want
this, it's is my team.
(rock music)
- Touchdown!
- [Narrator] In a historic
reversal of fortune,
the team scored five touchdowns
in the second quarter.
- [Announcer] Touchdown!
Washington takes the lead!
- Everything we called worked.
- [Announcer] He's got Sanders
in the clear at the ten.
Touchdown!
Touchdown, Washington Redskins.
(crowd roaring)
And a new Superbowl record.
- I remember him holding
that helmet up, (laughing)
when he scored 35 points
in the second quarter.
One of the greatest quarter of
a game in Superbowl history.
- [Announcer] Doug Williams,
the MVP of Superbowl XXII.
- [Narrator] Williams was
the first black quarterback
to start or win a Superbowl
and was crowned the game's
most valuable player.
- It was one of those
times that I raised my hat
and thinking to myself, you know,
I'd really like to tell
some people where to go
but it wasn't in my nature to do it.
(upbeat music)
(crowd cheering)
- [Narrator] As the '80s drew to a close,
Barry's lifestyle continued
to make headlines.
- At no time did I see any drugs,
use any drugs, or have any
knowledge of any drugs.
That little white powder is so powerful
it causes you to do things you
never thought you would do.
- [Narrator] The FBI uncovered
more allegations of drug use
and rampant corruption
among Barry's staff,
and that included deputy
mayor Ivanhoe Donaldson.
- I have been tried, convicted, sentenced
and doing time by some
members of the media.
- [Woman] I think Marion was very good
about playing the victim.
- Somebody set him up, (laughs)
somebody was picking on him.
- He didn't have the discipline
to stick to virtually anything.
I've heard more from Barry about
how he's gonna behave better
than I have from my own son.
- [Narrator] Despite it all,
Barry retained a grip on power,
kept afloat by his populist appeal.
- I think that some
black folks in the city
really thought that people
were going after Marion
because he was black,
and I don't think that
was necessarily the case.
- I'm a very controversial
person because I speak out.
But on the other hand, I'm
loved by a lot of people.
In fact people say
dang Barry, you're the
best mayor we ever had.
They're telling the truth, too. (laughing)
- [Narrator] Marion Barry
dominated Washington in the '80s.
- He was the sun around
which we all orbited.
The good things, the bad things.
- [Narrator] But even though the city
and the mayor's early
promise were now lost
among dysfunction and decay,
residents departed the
'80s with good memories
and optimism for the future.
- You could do 60 miles
an hour up Mass Avenue
and nobody would blink an eye over it.
- My kids who grew up
in the middle of that
look back fondly on their younger days.
I'll never forget when they graduated
they said we know the
best part of our lives
are probably behind us right now.
♪ Ooh shake it ♪
- Danger's exciting.
There was lots of opportunity
for art to spring up
like little flowers in the garden
and it was a wonderful combination.
(slow hip-hop music)
♪ Keep on movin' ♪
♪ Don't stop like the hands of time ♪
♪ Click clock ♪
♪ Find your own way to stay ♪
♪ The time will come one day ♪
♪ Why do people ♪
♪ Choose to live their lives ♪
- [Man] She did what?
♪ This way ♪
♪ Keep on movin' don't stop, no ♪
♪ Keep on movin' ♪
♪ Oh ♪
- [Narrator] Discover more
about Washington in the '80s
at weta.org.
- [Announcer] The mysteries
of Egypt's Great Pyramid.
- We need to know about
the people who built them.
Where is their settlement?
- [Announcer] Now, stunning discoveries--
- There's a void right through this wall.
- [Announcer] Are Decoding
the Great Pyramid on Nova.
- [Woman] Tonight at nine on TV 26.
- Franco had an idea
of the authentic Spain.
All of these things were
challenged by the left.
- Franco believed that he
should eliminate the left
and their ideology.
- Franco never lost a
minute's sleep over the crimes
that were committed in his name.
(dramatic music)
- [Announcer] Tonight at 10 on TV 26.
- [Narrator] Only about
250 of them were made.
Is this rare vase worth a fortune?
See what's in store this week
on a new season of Antiques Roadshow.
(jolly music)
- [Announcer] Tonight, they're the wild's
most ruthless predators.
Examine their fight to
survive in the Arctic North
with Nature at eight,
then see how the Egyptians
built the Great Pyramids with NOVA
and examine the life of Francisco Franco,
The Dictator's Playbook, tonight.
And our WETA UK channel, a new
season of Midsomer Murders,
then it was North America's
first school for secret agents, Camp X,
followed by an all new Bletchley Circle.
British television at its best.
(upbeat jazz music)
- [Narrator] Celebrate Black History Month
with WETA TV 26 next.
(uplifting orchestral music)