- [Reporter] That his brother's gambling
had placed his family in danger.
- [Reporter] Was it revenge
or was his graphic novel
a script for murder.
- It's just more like a horror movie.
- [Announcer] CBS News,
Original Reporting.
(upbeat music)
- [Announcer] Do you feel
the need to keep climbing,
even when you've reached the top?
Do you appreciate everything you have,
but still wanna do more?
You do when you're free.
Set yourself free in a Jeep Grand Cherokee
at the Jeep Fourth of July Sales Event.
Finance and get 4,250 total cash allowance
on select 2019 Jeep Grand
Cherokee models in dealer stock.
- [Zo] Right now at 11:00
heavy rain and strong winds
across the Washington area
tonight knocking down trees
and knocking out power.
These storms were
intense so let's find out
if we're in the clear.
Meteorologist, Melissa
Nord, is here with me now
and, Melissa, I have a
feeling the answer is no.
- Well, you're guessing right.
Mother Nature's storm
game is still going strong
at 11 o'clock tonight.
You can see the progression of the storms
over the last five hours
and just in the last hour
tracking another intense thunderstorm
that's over Southern Maryland,
stretching through Charles County
and now moving into St.
Mary's County, Mechanicsville,
with a lot of heavy rain and
about 20 lightening strikes
in the last 10 minutes alone.
So this is our one last
storm of the night.
Moving towards Lexington Park, 11:36
and if it holds together,
Ridge, Maryland by about midnight tonight.
Now tomorrow we have
another round of storms
so let's talk about storm threats.
Now tomorrow I think the
greater overall threat
is gonna end up being
just some very heavy rain
falling on saturated ground
that could lead to flooding.
We're gonna see lightening
and I think we could also
see an isolated storm
become strong or severe,
maybe not as many as we saw today,
but the storms tomorrow
will still be intense.
We'll start the morning with patchy fog.
Let' take Futurecast out to noon.
You're still noticing we're
mostly dry on Futurecast,
but starting in the afternoon
that next round of storms
starts firing up and,
Zo, once it starts going
it's gonna get only
more intense from there.
We'll take you through the
rest of the Futurecast.
We're gonna look ahead into
when we'll see our next streak
of dry days next.
- [Zo] That's what I wanna hear.
All right, thank you Melissa.
And this should come as no surprise,
the storms left behind a lot
of damage in our area tonight.
Check out this huge tree
that may have brushed against this house
along Reservoir Road in Northwest D.C.
right before falling over.
There's no word of any injuries tonight.
And in Glover Park more damage.
This tree snapped and fell
right onto that parked SUV.
Some of those other cars nearby
may have been damaged as well.
And check this out, also in the district
yet another tree crashes onto a car.
You can't even really see the car
because that tree is so big there.
This happened along Upshur Street
and New Hampshire Avenue.
And here's a look at more weather pictures
coming in tonight from our WUSA9 team
throughout the region.
These are just spectacular.
Look at this, because of the
intensity of this storm again
which you can gauge
from these images alone,
many people are without power tonight
especially in Prince George's County,
hundreds of people there without power.
Well, if you have pictures or video
you'd like to send our way you can tag us,
WUSA9 on Facebook or Twitter
and we'll share them here.
Well, before the storms rolled in tonight
police responded to a
deadly motorcycle crash
in Montgomery County.
This happened in
Gaithersburg just off of 270
at the intersection of 370 and Route 200.
Police tell us a 45-year-old
man crashed there tonight.
Well, it has certainly been
a tense day and night in Washington.
Right and left wing protestors,
they faced off near the White House today.
One side demanding free speech,
the other, speech free of hate.
Here's Jess Arnold.
- [Protestors] Build that wall.
- [Protestors] Black Lives Matter.
- [Jess] Right wing ralliers,
and counter protestors in
downtown D.C. Saturday.
- My biggest issue is the fact
that Trump is trying to divide people.
- I respect your conviction.
- [Man] Yes.
(background talking)
- [Jess] From MAGA-hat wearers
to the Neo-fascist group, Proud Boys,
the right rally to defend free speech
after they say sites
like Twitter and Facebook
censored some of them.
- [Woman] Will they take
away our right to Tweet,
take away our right to share photos,
take away our right to
share our peace of mind.
They take away our right to
do rallies like this, so.
- [Jess] Across the street groups like,
Black Lives Matter, Sanctuary DMV,
and other activists
joined under the banner,
AllOUTDC, to protest
hate in Pershing Park.
- We're over here showing that, you know,
even in the face of
white supremacy and hate
that we still are working
towards liberation.
- [Jess] Some clashes were inevitable.
- Do not touch me.
- Abraham Lincoln (mic
not picking up voice).
- It's not the party of
Abraham Lincoln anymore.
- Yes it is.
It is the party of (mumbles).
- These big tech companies they lie
and they call us Nazi's,
they call us terrible people,
they say all conservatives
are evil and racist.
To these Antifa people over there
have the complete wrong idea.
These Antifa people should be on our side.
If they're against fascism
they should be against censoring voices.
- [Jess] Those for and
against the President
had no problem raising
their voices Saturday.
- I support Donald Trump because of
the urban revitalization,
tax cuts, prison reform,
second-chance hiring,
that helps a black community a lot.
- I'm really ashamed
of a lot of the things
that are going on in the country
and I think it's really important
for everybody to speak out.
- [Man] Our street.
- [Together] Our street.
- [Jess] Jess Arnold, WUSA9.
- [Zo] Also tonight, still can't get over
these pictures right here.
Crews, they finally
removed that red minivan
that was swallowed up by
this massive sink hole
in Northern Virginia earlier this week.
This took place along Princedale Drive
in Woodbridge on the Fourth of July.
Thankfully that was just parked
and no one was inside at the time.
The Virginia Department of Transportation
is blaming a stormwater pipe that burst
because of all the rain
we've been getting lately.
While the van is now out VDOT says
it will take weeks to repair
this section of Princedale Drive
so it will remain closed.
And new details tonight
on a single-car crash
that shut down parts of I-95
in Spotsylvania County yesterday.
Some of you may have
been caught up in this
at the end of the workday.
We're now told a 2004 Ford Explorer
was traveling north on I-95
when the driver ran off the right shoulder
and overturned several times
before coming to a rest
on the left shoulder.
The driver, 24-year-old,
Jahvante Winnagle,
from West Virginia, was
taken to a nearby hospital
with life-threatening injuries,
but the news is more grim
for some of his passengers.
A passenger in that Ford,
47-year-old, Frederick Thomas,
was ejected and died at the scene.
Thomas was not wearing a seatbelt.
Another passenger, Robert
Rutherford, was also killed.
Now two other passengers
in that car with them
were transported to
Mary Washington Hospital
with minor injuries.
Both of those passengers
were wearing seat belts.
A suspected gas explosion in Florida today
reduced parts of a
shopping mall to rubble.
That blast was massive.
At least 21 people were hurt.
This happened in Plantation, Florida
west of Fort Lauderdale.
Here's, Peter King.
- [Peter] The blast originated
inside a vacant pizza
restaurant destroying it
and sending debris flying
across this shopping center
in Plantation, Florida.
Falling debris crushed several
cars in the parking lot.
- I heard a loud, boom, and really thought
it was fireworks.
- [Peter] The force of the
blast shattered windows
and damaged businesses in
the same section of the plaza
including an L.A. Fitness Center.
People inside the gym said
the entire building shook.
It's roof collapsed,
patrons were sent scrambling to get out.
- My first initial instinct was,
was this an earthquake, but I was like,
I'm in Florida so obviously
it's not an earthquake.
I was just terrified honestly.
- [Peter] The explosion
was powerful enough
to be felt for miles around.
- When we arrived we
found patients scattered
all about the debris area.
- [Peter] First responders
set up a triage area
and firefighters with
specially trained dogs
searched the area to make sure
no one was trapped or killed.
Fire officials say everyone
has been accounted for.
- We're very much relieved,
that considering the debris field,
and considering how we found the patients
and where we found 'em,
that the injuries are not as severe
as we would have thought they would be.
So we're very thankful for that.
- [Peter] Peter King, CBS News, Orlando.
- [Zo] President Trump doubling down
on his fight to add a
controversial question
about citizenship to the 2020 census.
Nicole Killian is traveling
with the President tonight
and she's in Berkeley Heights, New Jersey.
- [Nicole] President
Trump flew to New Jersey
for his first summer
visit to his country club.
While back in Washington aides scrambled
to find a way to get
a citizenship question
included in the 2020 census
despite pushback from the Supreme Court.
- We have four or five ways we could do it
so we're working on a lot of things
including an executive order.
- [Nicole] A source familiar
with the deliberations
tells CBS News attorneys are
reviewing all the options
and are trying to resolve the legal issues
as quickly as possible.
(background chanting)
Critics charge the citizenship question
discriminates against immigrants
and communities of color.
- We're gonna lose a lot of support
for the, our communities in our regions.
Experts say the President can't override
the Supreme Courts decision
to block the question,
but he can come up with a new rationale
for why it's warranted.
- The Commerce Secretary
can add some questions
to the census if there are
valid reasons to do so.
- [Nicole] The President also
wants action on immigration.
After postponing mass
deportation roundups last month
he's threatening they'll
start fairly soon.
- I don't call 'em raids,
I say they came in illegally
and we're bringing 'em out legally.
- [Nicole] The administration continues
to come under fire for poor conditions
at migrant detention centers
along the Southern border.
- President Trump claims
the facilities are clean
and run beautifully, but a
government watch dog report
described the crisis
as a ticking time bomb.
House Democrats plan a hearing next week.
Nicole Killian, CBS News,
Berkeley Heights, New Jersey.
- [Zo] Still ahead here tonight
if you like burgers
you're gonna wanna hear
about some of the tastiest
burgers in the nation
and find out why they're being
cooked up for a good cause.
- Thousands of earthquakes
have struck Southern California
in the last couple of days
with one reaching a 7.l magnitude.
I'm Joy Benedict in Pasadena, California
where scientist are trying to predict
just how long this shaking will last.
(upbeat orchestral music)
- [Announcer] WUSA9 News is
sponsored in part by Fios.
Choose Fios and get the best
on the 100% fiberoptic network.
Go to, getfios.com to switch today.
- Check out my Playscape
two-piece sectional.
The 799 price tag makes it great.
The two colors and five decorative pillows
makes it greater.
The comfy pop-up sleeper
with Bobapedic memory foam
makes it greaterer.
- [Together] Get Bob's Discount.
- [Man] Only at Bob's Discount Furniture.
- House for sale.
- Home for sale.
- Home for sale, home for sale.
- We've got a home.
- Available now.
- [Announcer] Cirque du
Soleil presents, Volta.
An energetic story of transformation
inspired by the adventurous
spirit of freedom.
Volta, opens July 26th under
the big top at Tysons II.
Tickets at cirquedusoleil.com.
- [Announcer] When you
get right down to it
freedom is the ability to
go where you want to go
and do what you want to do.
So grab a Jeep Compass and roam free
at the Jeep Fourth of July Sales Event.
Right now get $4,000 total cash allowance
on select 2019 Jeep Compass
models in dealer stock.
- My Caleb sofa and loveseat.
With Bob's Discount you get both pieces
for just 799.
- 799, are you joking?
- Do I look like I'm joking?
- Yes, you look like you're joking.
- I'm serious.
- Cool.
- [Together] Get Bob's Discount.
- Aw man, this is what
people are dealing with
out West tonight.
We are learning about a strong earthquake
that jolted the Los
Angeles area last night
just a day after a slightly weaker one
rattled Southern California.
The magnitude 7.1 earthquake's epicenter
is near Ridgecrest where a rock slide
has shut down a road.
It also triggered a number of fires.
Here's, Joy Benedict, in Pasadena.
- [Joy] The magnitude 7.1 earthquake
hit just one day after Thursdays 6.4 jolt.
- There were a number of structure fires,
there were gas leaks,
there was road damage,
rock slides.
- [Joy] This was the scene
inside a market in Ridgecrest,
the city near the epicenter of the quakes.
Food and other items flew off the shelves.
- This is a very strong earthquake.
- [Joy] About 150 miles to the Southwest
our CBS colleagues in Los Angeles
felt the earthquake Friday night
while they were broadcasting.
- We'll be right back.
- Wow.
- [Joy] And at the Dodgers home game.
- Suddenly like something started shaking
and we're like looking
around and all of a sudden
everyone's like, whoa.
- [Joy] But the baseball game continued.
The earthquake even rattled Los Vegas
with enough force to stop this NBA game.
Thousands of earthquakes have
struck Southern California
here in the last couple of days
so scientists here at Cal
Tech are crunching the numbers
trying to figure out
the probability of more.
- We're concerned about future aftershocks
and where they're gonna be.
- [Joy] Seismologists say the likelihood
of another magnitude six
quake over the next week
is more than 25%.
Joy Benedict, CBS News,
Pasadena, California.
- And Governor Gavin Newsom
declared a state of emergency
for a section of Southern California
that saw significant damage
after Friday night's earthquake.
All right I wanna bring in
meteorologist, Melissa Nord,
again with us tonight
because it's been a busy night
storm wise--
- Yep.
- And it's still not over.
- It's not over quite yet.
- Okay.
- We've got one storm
that is left out there,
but we get--
- Just one.
- To do it all
again tomorrow.
- Rinse and repeat, right?
- As if you were not done with it already.
Here we go, look at the tower cam,
nice and dry over D.C. right now.
I don't remember if I mentioned
this a couple minutes ago,
our wind gusts at Reagan National,
as the storms were coming through,
was just about 40 miles an hour,
but at the Capitol it gusted to 66.
That's why there's
dozens, I'm not kidding,
66 at the U.S. Capitol.
It's not, but in terms
of a, it can happen,
we'll just leave it there.
There were dozens of
trees down all over D.C.
At one point we had about
5,000 people without power
in Bladen County, 4,000
people without power
in Prince George's County,
hopefully all of your power
is restored at this point.
But let me show you the
last remaining storm
with still a lot of lightening
over Southern Charles
County and now really
into St. Mary's County.
I put a lightening tracker on this
and for 11 o'clock at night
this storm is holding together pretty well
with heavy rain right over Mechanicsville
moving into Leonardtown.
About 45 lightening strikes
in the last 10 minutes alone.
Here's the setup though.
We've got this front that
is trying to move through,
but it is gonna stall out
over the area tomorrow.
That front is the dividing line between
this disgustingly humid
air mass we've been in
and, well, not exactly
Canadian pleasantry,
but it'll be a little drop in the humidity
a little more manageable
levels outside by Tuesday.
But we're in that transition
period for Sunday and Monday
with still some storm chances.
So I pulled up here a
different weather model
showing you over the next 48
hours alone, look at this.
I mean, we've got our
in-house RPM model showing
we could get another 3 1/2
inches in some isolated spots.
So what this is showing me is
we have a heavy rainfall
threat setting up for tomorrow.
Tomorrow's storms could bring
some locally heavy rain.
That is my biggest concern
out of all of our storm threats.
Yes, I think we could see
an isolated strong severe storm tomorrow,
like we saw today, but not
quite as many strong storms
with some damaging winds.
But I think the overall
greater threat for tomorrow
is gonna be some downpours
falling on saturated ground
and that could lead to flooding.
We're also gonna see lightening.
So if you're gonna be
boating, at the pool,
just hiking outside
tomorrow, or enjoying brunch,
heads up, there will be some storms.
You don't wanna be
caught outside with them.
Okay, Futurecast hour-by-hour.
Now after today's storms I
do think we're going to see
some fog forming
overnight, some of that fog
could be locally dense.
So we'll start the
morning with cloud cover
with some patchy fog, temps in the 70s.
By lunchtime still a bit of cloud cover,
but we're starting to see
that cloud cover breaking
up a bit, temps in the 80s.
We head into 3:00 in the afternoon
and here's where we start to see
those scattered storms developing
and I think our storm timeframe tomorrow
is a little bit later than it was today.
Storms will start around mid afternoon,
they'll really ramp up
as we head past dinnertime in the evening.
Lots of my computer models
are trying to keep storms in the forecast
throughout Sunday night and
even in to Monday morning,
but with a lot of heavy
storms that keep bringing
rounds of heavy rain over the area,
that's why I think
tomorrow's gonna be flooding
a bigger threat locally,
especially street flooding
and creek and stream levels rising.
So tomorrow we start with that patchy fog,
a mostly dry start to the day,
but it's later in the
day we start to bring
those storm chances in.
I've got highs that are
running in the mid 80s.
All right, Nats forecast for tomorrow.
They're playing Kansas City
Royals, 1:35 first pitch.
You know I think we're
gonna get pretty lucky
at the beginning of things,
but by the end of the game we'll track
some of those wildly scattered storms
so by the finish of the
game, yeah, it's possible,
there could be a rain delay.
But I think a, cross your fingers,
1:35 looks like a better
start time tomorrow
than having something
middle of the afternoon.
All right, so tomorrow,
here's our showers and thunderstorms.
We'll go into Monday and that front
is still close enough to us
to where it leaves us
with some storm chances,
but as we get into Tuesday and Wednesday
that high pressure
completely dries us out,
it brings in a slightly lower humidity.
So overall our forecast becomes
a lot more manageable outside
in terms of humidity and storm chances
Tuesday and Wednesday into this week.
By the way, Tracking
the Tropics, this week.
20% chance we could have a system develop.
It's actually an upper level trough
which is over Western Tennessee,
but it's gonna move out to the Gulf
and this is the area we're gonna watch
for some heavy rainfall
set up shop into this week.
So if you're taking a vacation out towards
PCB, Panama City Beach, Pensacola,
even over to New Orleans,
that's what I'm tracking
this week in the tropics.
All right I lowered the
high temp tomorrow to 88.
I think a bit of cloud
cover, fog, in the morning
is gonna limit how high we get,
but it's humid with some
thunderstorms late in the day
and into tomorrow night.
A few more storms Monday,
dry Tuesday, dry Wednesday.
We'll bring back some
storm chances Thursday
and lower humidity returns on Friday, Zo.
- All right, thank you Melissa.
Well, if you have an appetite for burgers
the place to be this holiday
weekend is Wisconsin.
I know you're not gonna
like me after this,
going to bed, not thinking about food,
and then I show you this juiciness.
The chef's at Riverfest are offering up
some of of the tastiest
burgers anywhere, so they say.
It's the fourth annual
Burger Bash, and get this,
for 10 bucks people can sample burgers
from competing chefs in
Wisconsin, Minnesota, and Iowa,
and then vote for who should
win the People's Choice Award
and a $300 reward.
Member's of local
organizations, and chefs,
they made up a panel of judges
that decided the best burger..
- This is definitely a competition.
Our chefs take this seriously,
our judges take this seriously.
When the community comes in
and they give their input
the chefs really like to
know what people think
of their, of their recipes.
- [Zo] I love seeing the people behind her
they look so happy.
Proceeds from the event will go to the,
Beer By Bike Brigade's fundraiser
to pay down school lunch debt for kids.
All right, coming up
next the NBA finals' MVP
is moving on, what's
next for Kawhi Leonard.
Plus a unique obstacle
course featuring couples
racing for a world championship.
We'll tell you about this one next.
- Don't I got rights?
I said I don't consent to search.
- This stop led to a complaint
against D.C. police.
Last year there were 780
of them, a new record,
but some in the department say,
it's not the officer's fault.
Who's policing the police?
Tuesday at 11:00.
- [Announcer] When does
an opportunity become
a golden opportunity?
When a forward-thinking safety system
and peace of mind meet exceptional offers.
Don't miss your golden opportunity
to experience our most
advanced safety technology
now at the Lexus Golden
Opportunity Sales Event.
- [Announcer] Lease the 2019 ES 350
for 379 a month for 36 months
and we'll make your first month's payment.
- [Announcer] Experience,
amazing, at your Lexus dealer.
- We are sisters and we
just moved in together.
- [Announcer] Why Alissa
and Aleah chose Fios.
- We stream so much.
A lot of times Alissa is
watching TV on her laptop,
using her phone, also using
her tablet.
- I am really
good at multitasking,
cause I'm awesome.
- A little.
(laughing)
- [Announcer] The best
internet is even better
at our best price.
Switch now and get our
fastest speeds available
plus a free Chromebook on us.
That's Fios.
- [Announcer] It's the Final Days
of our 4th of July Sales Event.
Your last chance to get great deals
on our Ford SUV lineup.
Now get 0% financing for
72 months on Ford Explorer,
or 0% for 60 months on
Escape, Edge, and Expedition.
It's no wonder Ford SUV's
have the highest brand
loyalty in the industry.
During Final Days get 0% financing
for 72 months on Explorer.
Get zero for 60 on Escape,
Edge, and Expedition,
or choose $8,400 in total
savings on Ford Edge.
- [Announcer] This is not a bed,
it's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
Smart Bed is on sale now
during our lowest prices of the season.
It senses your movement
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
It even helps with this.
So you wake up ready to
hit the ground running.
Don't miss our 4th of July Special
for the queen Sleep Number
360 c4 Smart Bed now 1,299,
plus free premium delivery
when you add a base.
Ends Sunday.
Sleep Number, proven quality sleep.
- [Announcer] How do you win over fans?
You give them something they love.
Something no one else can.
Something they can't get enough of.
And then you give them more.
Hurry in to see why Ram has
the most loyal half-ton pickup owners
during the Ram Summer Clearance Event.
- [Announcer] Now get 20% off MSRP
on select 2019 Ram 1500
Classic models in dealer stock.
- [Announcer] And now, WUSA9 Sports
brought to you by XFINITY.
- All right, take a close
look at this right here.
All the Nationals the
uniforms they wore today,
there was a powder-blue
kind of jersey there,
and the pants that the Montreal Expos wore
through their inaugural
season 50 years ago.
It's the first time the
Nats wore these Expos,
throw-back uniforms, if you will.
As for the game.
- [Announcer] Kurt Suzuki, deep to left,
see, you, later.
Above the bullpen.
What a great combination to a long at-bat,
three-nothing, Nats.
- See, you, later, no, no.
Melissa was supposed to
join in with me on that one,
left me hanging.
All right that two-run
blast was more than enough.
Support from Max Scherzer who picked up
his ninth win of the season.
The Nats shut out Kansas
City six to nothing.
And Nationals' third
baseman, Anthony Rendon,
will not play in the All-Star game.
He says he's dealing
with some minor ailments
and he needs a little
time to rest and heal.
We wish him well.
All right, the Orioles
are in Canada this weekend
to wrap up the first half of the season.
- [Announcer] And delivered,
boy did he get that one,
way back left field and it is, gone.
Goodbye home run it stayed.
So the Orioles slide to that foul pole.
And Nunez cranks one.
A couple of RBI's and a
two-nothing lead for the Orioles.
- Yeah, and that two-run blast
was part of a five-run, fourth,
that helped Baltimore beat
the Blue Jays, eight to one.
The Birds have now won
three in a row, keep going.
All right and we are just hearing tonight
that the Washington Wizards
have acquired forward,
Davis Bertans, from San Antonio,
in a three-team deal with
the Spurs and the Nets.
The Wizards sent the
draft rights of forward,
Aaron White, to Brooklyn
and the Spurs acquired,
DeMarre Carroll from Brooklyn.
All right, well dramatic changes
to the landscape of the NBA.
The Los Angeles Clippers
reportedly made two big moves.
They're signing free agent, Kawhi Leonard,
to a four-year, 142
million dollar contract.
While completing a trade
with the Oklahoma City
Thunder for Paul George.
Leonard becomes the first
player ever to switch teams
right after winning the finals MVP.
Getting paid nicely too.
And, you know, maybe they just needed
some time to cool off a bit,
but they probably didn't wanna be blasted
with sprinklers like this.
A mixed-doubles match at Wimbledon
was interrupted when a
sprinkler just went off,
blasting those players who
were sitting on the bench
during the change-over.
Yeah, not fun at all, right?
Of course they're quick too.
All right, and they're off in this case.
A blast of a traditional firework
kicked off, Pamplona, Spain,
Running of the Bulls Festival
opening nine days of
uninterrupted partying.
How 'bout that?
A member of the Northern
city's official brass band
was chosen this year
for Saturday's launch of the rocket,
known as the Chupinazo,
to mark 100 years since the
local ensemble's foundation.
You can see revelers there,
they're dressed in their white attire,
flaunting those traditional red scarves,
who just spray each other with wine.
They'd have a good time too.
American novelist, Ernest Hemingway,
immortalized the fiesta that each year
draws around 100, or one million visitors
for eight consecutive
mornings starting Sunday.
These dare devils they race with the bulls
along a 930 yard street course
to the city's bullring.
(crowd cheering and hollering)
Uh, never.
All right, now another kind of race here.
A Lithuanian man and his wife
they've won the world's
Wife-Carrying title, okay,
leaping over timber, wading
through waist-high water
to beat dozens of other couples
for a second year running.
The couple cleared a grueling
278-yard obstacle course
in one minute 6.72 seconds.
That was just a tenth of a second ahead of
the former six-time world
champion and his partner.
Couples from over a dozen countries,
they take part in this
annual race in Finland
and prizes were issued
to the first three couples
to cross the finish line,
as well as the most entertaining couple,
best costume, and the strongest carrier.
Can you get over this video, this is wild,
wild stuff right here.
Well, despite the event's name
couples do not have to be married.
Relationship-building exercise right here.
All right, still ahead,
heavy rain tonight.
What can we expect Sunday and
heading into your work week.
Well, Melissa is back
with the latest, next.
- [Announcer] Mattress
Firm's 4th of July Sale
has been extended.
Get a free adjustable base,
two free memory-foam pillows,
and a free mattress protector
when you take home your
new bed for just 799.
That's a value of over 850 free.
Your budget stretches
further at Mattress Firm.
(door banging shut)
- It's all clear.
- Hey sheep, give me a beat.
(putt, putt, putt, putt, putt)
♪ Yeah, everybody say, hey. ♪
♪ Hey. ♪
♪ Everybody say, oo-o. ♪
♪ Oo-o. ♪
♪ Go Woody, go Woody. ♪
- Ha-ho.
- Yeah.
- [Announcer] Hurry in
to the Chrysler Fourth of July Sales Event
where great deals come to life
on the Pacifica and the Pacifica Hybrid.
See Disney Pixar's, Toy
Story 4, in theaters now.
Get 0% financing, plus
3,750 total bonus cash,
plus no monthly payments for 90 days
on the 2019 Pacifica.
- Honey this Gig-speed
internet is ridiculously fast.
We are seriously keeping
up with the Jones'.
- Keeping up with the Ford's.
- Keeping up with the Garcia's.
- The Ramero's.
- The Tow's.
- Walansky's.
- No one's gonna have internet like this.
- [Announcer] Xfinity makes
keeping up with the Jones'
simple, easy, awesome.
Want Gig-speed internet?
We've got you covered.
Or check out our other
amazing speed options
at new low prices.
Get started now for as
low as 29.99 a month.
Call, click, or visit a store today.
- [Announcer] It's the Final Days
of our 4th of July Sales Event.
Don't miss your last chance for huge deals
on F-Series, America's best-selling trucks
for 42 years straight.
Get 0% APR financing for 72
months on the Ford F-150,
or check out the all new 2019 Ford Ranger,
and see why it's the
ultimate adventure gear.
During Final Days get 0%
for 72 months on Ford F-150.
And if you've ever served in the military,
or are a first responder,
get 1500 more in appreciation cash
on these Ford trucks on top of all offers.
- Okay, have fun at your dad's.
- [Boy] Okay, I love you mom.
- Bye.
- What do you think?
- I like it.
- Get up.
- Come on, got it.
- Yes.
- [Dad] You hungry?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Bye dad.
- Bye buddy.
- [Mom] How was it?
- Dad's internet is amazing.
- Well, you know, mom's
cookies are also amazing.
That's what I thought.
- [Announcer] Get up to 1 GIG speeds
on the day you move in.
Cox internet starting at 29.99 per month
for up to 10 megs.
- [Announcer] Do you feel
the need to keep climbing
even when you've reached the top?
Do you appreciate everything you have,
but still wanna do more?
You do when you're free.
Set yourself free in a Jeep Grand Cherokee
at the Jeep Fourth of July Sales Event.
Financing, get 4,250 total cash allowance
on select 2019 Jeep Grand
Cherokee models in dealer stock.
- [Announcer] Mattress Firm is extending
our, Free, Free, Free Event.
Celebrate and turn your
mattress into a bed
with free accessories.
Like a free adjustable base,
and more when you take home
your new bed for just 799.
Plus save up to $400 store wide.
Your budget stretches
further at Mattress Firm.
- Rain or shine trust DC's
most accurate forecast
only on WUSA9.
- You know, just still waitin' around
for that cool summer
day, no rain, no storms,
just sunshine.
- Fall.
- Fall, no, now you're taking it too far.
We want summer--
- I know.
- But, you know just not
these storms.
- I know, people are
sick of it.
This is fourth of July for
us here.
- Yeah.
- In typical fashion for us in D.C.
We're gonna have another round
of some scattered showers
and storms late tomorrow.
Some of them could bring
some very heavy rainfall.
Isolated strong severe storm.
I think those storms actually
carry into Sunday night.
Another round of some
storms possible on Monday.
I think your pick of the week, Zo,
is going to be Tuesday.
- Tuesday?
- [Melissa] A little
lower humidity, it's dry,
it's sunny and-
- I'll take what I can get.
- And more storms on Thursday.
We could just go through the week by week.
You know what though, I
know it sucks for Nats fans,
like when there's rain delays,
but next Friday's game
actually looks really good.
- Good, okay, okay.
- Yeah.
- I was a game, I think two weeks ago,
and it got rained out,
so here we go, of course.
Thank you for being here with us
for the news at 11:00.
We'll see you back here tomorrow
night, have a great night.
- [Announcer] You've
been watching WUSA9 News
with a weather forecast
rated, most accurate
for the last seven years.
- [Announcer] The 2019
Escalade is made for summer,
and made to move.
Get 0% APR for 72 months plus $1,000
on a 2019 Cadillac Escalade
when you finance through GM Financial.
- Everyone loves a throw-back,
but I haven't worn that suit in awhile,
or those shoes.
Luckily I still have them
because the clothes that
once gave you comfort
can help someone get their
career back on track.
So throw-back and donate
at Men's Wearhouse today.
- [Announcer] It's a
long 4th of July weekend
which means more time to
check out your favorite Kias.
All of our amazing vehicles come with
a 10-year, 100,000 mile warranty
and advanced technology features.
And during our Summer Sticker Sales Event
hurry in to get 0% APR for 66 months
and up $2,000 additional cash
on specially tagged 2019 vehicles.
Visit your local Kia dealer,
look for a sticker, and save.
Hurry in this 4th of July weekend,
offer ends July 8th.
- Here's your Buick sir.
- Actually, that's my Buick.
- Your Buick doesn't have a roof rack.
- This is my Buick.
- [Boy] How are we gonna
fit in your mom's Buick?
- [Boy] Easy.
- I like that new Buick.
- Me too.
- I was actually talking about that Buick.
- I knew that.
- Did ya?
- [Announcer] Buick's fresh new lineup
is full of surprises.
During Buick's Fourth of July Sales Event
pay no interest for 76 months
on most 2019 Buick models.
("Dreams" by Haley Reinhart)
♪ And oh, my dreams ♪
♪ It's never quite as it seems ♪
♪ I know I felt like this before ♪
- [Announcer] Find
inspiration in every mile.
The Mazda CX-5 with turbo, feel alive.
Now get a 2019 Mazda Crossover
for 0.9% APR for 60 months.
- Let's play dare to compare.
My Bobapedic Signature gel queen mattress
versus the Tempur-Pedic TEMPUR-Adapt.
Both have cool-to-the-touch
cover and luxurious memory foam,
but my Bobapedic gel memory
foam is infused with cooling gel
plus the Signature is 13 1/2
inches thick versus their 11,
and has four layers of
foam to their three.
Oh!
And a 20-year warranty versus their 10.
And with Bob's Discount mine is just 899
and theirs is a whopping 2199,
$1300 less than theirs.
- [Together] Get Bob's Discount.
- [Announcer] Some see
trails as only muddy paths,
steep climbs, and rough terrain.
But in the redesigned Jeep Cherokee
you're trail can lead anywhere.
See where your trail leads
at the Jeep Fourth of July Sales Event.
Now financing at 5,750
total cash allowance
on select 2019 Jeep Cherokee
models in dealer stock.
- Everyone loves a throwback, but...