- [Nancy] The hill,
breaking down the
president's message of unity.
The picture problem of Governor
Ralph Northam's alma mater.
- Some are shockingly
racist, some are repugnant.
- [Nancy] It goes beyond
his infamous photo.
Tonight, the school's plan to make up
for it following the apology.
And cruise ship drug smuggling busted.
- It's when there's
three, 4,000 on a boat,
there's a lot of things going on.
- [Nancy] A DC drag queen's plan hatched
on his government computer.
(upbeat, riveting music)
- [Announcer] Now, ABC 7
News at 6 On Your Side.
- And right now it's six
o'clock as we come on the air.
We're just three hours away now
from the delayed State
of the Union Address.
- The president uninvited
from delivering it a week ago
after that partial government shutdown.
Chief political correspondent Scott Thuman
joins us live on the Hill.
And, Scott, what can we
expect to hear tonight?
- Well, look, the president's going to try
and sell a message of unity,
of some sort of bipartisanship,
trying to get both sides of the
aisle to agree on something.
He knows that, with Democrats
in power here in the House,
that he has to get some of them on board
if he's going to pass any legislation.
He also knows the idea
of selling optimism can be very tough,
especially considering
the environment here.
(House applauds)
When President Trump takes
center stage Tuesday night,
he'll call for unity and bipartisanship.
The latest immigration fight
is proof there's been little
to go around lately but no
shortage of finger pointing.
So what can he do?
- He's calling for
bipartisanship and unity,
and we're compromising
cooperation and less divisiveness,
retribution politics, as he calls it.
- [Scott] Common ground could be found
over lowering prescription drug costs
or approving shovel-ready projects
for an aging infrastructure.
- Frankly, he made almost
identical statements last year,
and the progress has been painfully small.
- [Scott] He'll have his
work cut out for him.
Skeptical Democrats now
hold power in the House,
and, after enduring a
35-day government shutdown,
the third of his presidency,
he has just 10 days
from a possible fourth.
- He's shown that he's
pretty good at dividing.
I think it's time to demonstrate
he's good at uniting.
- [Scott] From trade to troop movements
to the ultimate controversy, the wall,
healing wounds and
coalescing with Congress
could be his greatest challenge
or greatest victory so far.
- I see that in my polling,
I see it as I travel the country.
The do wanna see both
parties work together,
and the president is
extending that olive branch.
We'll see if the Democrats will accept it.
- Now I just spoke with a
longtime Democratic congressman,
and I asked him is there
anywhere on the left,
are there any members on the left,
that the president can win over tonight?
He said flat out no, that
that is not an option,
that they have written
him off, essentially.
Now, that doesn't mean he couched it,
that they won't agree on legislation.
If they believe it benefits both of them,
if they believe they're
getting a fair shake,
they said they will work
with the White House.
But as far as getting anyone
to really cross the aisle,
that is going to be
very difficult tonight.
Reporting live in Statuary
Hall, I'm Scott Thuman.
Back to you.
- All right, Scott, thank you.
Now keep in mind, some
roads around the Capitol
already closed to pedestrians
at this hour; take a look.
Those are the ones you see
highlighted in red right there.
The ones in purple will close to drivers
in about an hour from now at seven.
Of course, most of the people
attending tonight's speech
will already be at the Capitol
once those roads close,
and that includes the first
person released from prison
as a result of the First
Step Prison Reform bill.
Matthew Charles served 35
years for selling crack.
- It's a remarkable experience.
I'm very humbled and grateful.
It's something I never could've
fathomed in a million years,
and it's happening, and I'm just thankful.
- [Nancy] The president's
guests also include the father
of one of the sailors killed
in the attack on the USS Cole.
- Now we will bring you the
complete State of the Union
and the Democratic response tonight,
starting at nine o'clock
right here on ABC 7
and our sister station, WJLA 24/7 News.
Then the coverage continues
on ABC 7 News at 11 o'clock.
In other news now, today, an
apology from the president
of the medical school the
Virginia's governor attended
after racist photos surfaced from one
of the school's yearbooks.
- But tonight, despite
intense political pressure,
there is no indication Ralph
Northam plans to step down.
Michelle Marsh begins our team
coverage now from Richmond.
- Nancy and John, in fact,
the protests have died down.
On the surface, it appeared
to be business as usual
inside the State House.
We saw lawmakers urgently working to push
through legislation on this
all-important crossover day.
We saw the lieutenant
governor, Justin Fairfax,
presiding over the Senate
as he normally does,
this just days after a 2004 allegation
of sexual assault resurfaced against him.
While he admits to a consensual encounter,
he denies he sexually assaulted anyone.
Governor Northam, meantime,
still under pressure to resign
after the discovery of
this racist yearbook photo
on his page from 1984.
- I cannot tell you
why he hasn't resigned,
but I am so praying that he would do that
and get it behind us.
- [Reporter] So you're still able
to get ahead with the legislative agenda
without any of these controversies
surrounding the governor
nor the lieutenant governor
affecting business?
- We have worked on the floor,
we've had debates on legislation,
we've talked about the things that matter,
and we'll continue to move forward.
- Now when it comes to that racist image
that appeared on Northam's yearbook page,
the university, Eastern
Virginia Medical School,
takes full responsibility for that.
They came out with that statement today.
Our Tim Barber was there
when the school addressed the issue.
(bright, chiming music)
- We are serious about finding
the facts of what happened.
- [Tim] 40 years after this photo
of Governor Northam's 1984
yearboook page resurfaced,
the provost of the governor's alma mater,
Eastern Virginia Medical School,
is launching an investigation in
why photos like this were ever allowed.
- Some are repugnant,
some are unprofessional,
some are shockingly
abhorrent, like I mentioned.
- [Tim] The investigation will be run
by former Virginia Attorney
General Richard Cullen,
who is also representing
the vice president
in Mueller's Russia probe.
Cullen will also look at
other controversial pictures,
such as these students in
Confederate uniforms from 2013,
pictures which prompted the provost
to put an end to yearbook production.
Governor Northam first
said he was in the photo
then denied it, then also
admitted to wearing blackface
during a dance competition.
- I believe you deserve
to hear directly from me.
- [Tim] While the governor
demands time to prove his past,
the medical school that
gave the governor his start
is examining its own.
- There are many circumstances
we need to clarify.
That's why we hired the independent
law firm to investigate.
- [Tim] Reporting in Norfolk, Virginia,
Tim Barber, ABC 7 News.
- Now while the governor may be trying
to win over those who
want him out of office
through time and regaining their trust,
we spoke to one lawmaker
today, Senator Lucas,
who says he needs to resign now.
Time will not make this issue better.
We do wanna urge you to stay with ABC 7
for our continuous
coverage here in Richmond
on this and watching for all developments
from the governor's mansion.
Download the free ABC 7 News app
to get push alerts and updates
whenever there is a new development.
That is the very latest from Richmond.
I'm Michelle Marsh; now back to you.
- [John] Okay, Michelle, thanks.
Update now on some breaking news
that we've been following
for over the last few hours.
It was a possible
transformer that exploded
and rattled a lot of nerves
in downtown Arlington.
It happened at North
Lynn and 19th Streets,
right in the heart of
Rosslyn leading right
up to Key Bridge, which is a major artery,
especially this time of day.
Now nobody was hurt,
but the fire department
did rescue people that were
trapped in some elevators
while the power was out.
All the roads now are back open tonight,
and nobody, we understand,
has been hurt, so that's good.
- [Nancy] An outpouring of support
in the last hour after five children
were killed in a horrific crash.
- Two local men are arrested
in Miami for allegedly trying
to sneak a vast amount of
drugs onto a cruise ship.
The story in a moment.
(bright, chiming music)
- And good evening, everyone.
I'm meteorologist Bill Kelly.
Normal high temperature
for today into the mid 40s.
Here we are in the six o'clock hour,
and we're still knocking
on the door of 70.
A record-breaking day,
and it may not be the only one this week.
We'll talk about that
coming up in just minutes.
(upbeat, riveting music)
- [Narrator] Don't miss
the President's Day Sale
at Furniture Max in
Fairfax and Falls Church.
- [Narrator] Imagine your
child being verbally attacked
at school like this.
- [Teacher] I'll punch you in your face.
- [Narrator] This local
mother fought back.
- That was the first day I
put the recorder in her hair.
- [Narrator] What 6 On Your Side found out
is only the tip of the iceberg.
Thursday at 11.
- I didn't realize how bad my smile was
with fillings and root canals.
I had to do something.
I looked at partial bridges,
I looked at dentures.
Out of all the options,
Clear Choice was the only choice for me.
- [Narrator] At Clear Choice,
we bring hope to millions
who suffer from missing or failing teeth
with dental implants that look, feel,
and function like strong, natural teeth.
- All the specialists with
all the technology they need
are in one spot.
It makes delivering this
21-century world-class dentistry
very easy to do, and we do it in one day.
- [Ron] I can laugh.
People crack a joke, and I smile.
It was a life-changing thing.
- [Narrator] Call today
to schedule your free
comprehensive consultation,
an iCAD 3D imaging scan.
We'll even talk financing
options while you're here.
- They not only helped rebuild my smile
but helped me to rebuild
my self confidence.
They really set me free.
Look at this smile.
- [Narrator] At Clear Choice,
you're about to discover
what you've been missing all these years.
Call Clear Choice today.
- I remember when I
first got to Baltimore.
A great teammate of mine, one
of the best football players I
ever known, he's not eating bad food.
He wasn't putting bad foods in his body.
He's like, man, if you want longevity,
you gotta make sure you're eating
and taking care of your
body a certain way.
If you order Terra's
Kitchen, you will learn more
about nutrition, it's gonna
be more healthier, it's fresh.
So you need to know what
you put into your body.
Terra's Kitchen, we know it.
♪ Just like fire ♪
- When you get to work,
turn on 97.1 WASHFM for two
hours of commercial-free music.
Two hours of nonstop
variety, starting at 8:40.
Washington's variety station, 97.1 WASHFM.
- Is your house less than perfect?
I'm Dan from MarketPro Homebuyers,
and we wanna buy your home.
- MarketPro Homebuyers
gave us a fair offer
and truly helped my family.
- [Dan] Call us today at 301-750-7355.
(metal door slams open)
- [Narrator] Six captains, six teams...
- And one million dollars.
- [Narrator] The Jeopardy All-Star Games,
starting February 20th at 7:30 at ABC 7.
- [Nancy] Tonight, 10 people dead
after this massive fire tore
through an apartment complex in Paris.
Some residents there
are climbing to the roof
of this nine-story building
just to try and escape.
A 40-year-old woman who
lived in that building
under arrest tonight.
Police say she has a
history of mental problems.
- [John] We're also getting
new information tonight
after that deadly plane
crash in California.
Police say the pilot may not have been
who he claimed to be.
Initial reports were that the 75 year old
was a retired police officer
from Chicago living in Nevada.
Today, though, the Chicago
Police Department came out
and said there's no record that he
was ever with their force.
Police are still trying to figure out
why that twin engine plane broke apart
over a Southern California neighborhood,
killing the pilot and four people
in a home celebrating the Super Bowl.
(bright, chiming music)
And only on 7, two men accused
of stealing half a million dollars
in copper from a Montgomery
County construction site.
The pipes and wiring
were taken in White Oak,
where the new Washington
Adventist Hospital will be built.
Police say that the men broke
into a fenced-off work area
10 times over a nine-month period.
They were caught after
police connected them
to the crime scene using
the GPS information
from their cell phones.
- Coming up at six...
(intense, dramatic music)
- His example of how
the Coast Guard delivers
mission excellence anytime and anywhere.
- [Nanccy] And even when
they're not being paid.
The Coast Guard's impressive work
during that partial government shutdown.
- [John] And less than 24 hours
after 7 On Your Side
brought you startling news
about insulin prices,
one local lawmaker says
that he wants to find out
why the drug costs so much.
(upbeat music)
- [Child] What is home?
Home is where everybody
can splash all day long,
be romantic, eww,
stay fit, learn new
recipes, start a business,
make a new friend, and ride
until the sun goes down
after you finish your homework.
Home; it's Potomac Shores,
the American way of life.
- [Announcer] Go global
and explore Green Front
in Manassas today.
♪ Just like fire ♪
- When you get to work,
turn on 97.1 WASHFM for two
hours of commercial-free music.
Two hours of nonstop
variety, starting at 8:40.
Washington's variety station, 97.1 WASHFM.
- [Narrator] Celebrity Cruises
was voted Best Premium Cruise Line
for the 11th year in a
row, and, to celebrate,
we're giving your our
best offer of the year.
For a limited time, get a
premium beverage package,
unlimited Wi-fi, prepaid tips,
and $150 dollars to spend on board,
plus savings up to $400
when you book a vacation
in Europe, Alaska, the
Caribbean, and beyond.
Offer ends Thursday.
Click or call to book today.
(pleasant piano music)
- This is a commercial about buying cars.
That's a car, this is a
phone, and this is Drive Time.
Do you need a car?
- Yes, but I don't have a lot of money.
- Oh, great!
Go online and check out Drive
Time and save that money!
Their down payments are
$1,000 less on average.
- Ooh, this is a car commercial.
(gasps) Will there be a phony focus group?
- Nope, just valuable information.
99% of people who apply get approved,
even if their credit is eh.
You can do it in two
minutes from anywhere.
All you need is your phone.
- I have a phone.
- Everybody does!
- Yeah, I'm done, I got approved!
- Go to drivetime.com and
get approved in two minutes.
Drive Time, genius!
- Justice.
Greenberg & Bederman has won justice
for thousands of personal injury victims
for more than 30 years, and we're here
to get justice for you as well.
If you've been in a car accident,
a victim of medical malpractice,
or denied Social Security
disability benefits,
we're here to help you regain
your dignity and respect
and receive the financial
compensation you deserve.