>> NOW ABC7 NEWS AT NOON.
ON YOUR SIDE.
>>Adrianna: AS A COME ON THE
AIR AT NOON.
RAIN IS STILL COMING DOWN
ENTERING THE START OF THE WORK
WEEK INTO A SLOPPY MESS.IT
WINTRY MIX THAT LEFT SNOW IN
SOME AREAS CAUSED SCHOOL DELAYS
THIS MORNING AND SOME CLOSURES.
THINGS ARE QUIETING DOWN BUT
STILL, THERE IS MORE RAIN TO
COME.
>>Steve: A LOT MORE RAIN ON THE
WAY TONIGHT INTO THE DAY
TOMORROW.
OUT NEAR DULLES INTERNATIONAL
AIRPORT AND LOOKING AT THE
WINTRY MIX AND WE DO HAVE A
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY NOW FOR
FREDERICK COUNTY AND WASHINGTON
COUNTY AND WESTERN MARYLAND.
THIS IS THROUGH THIS AFTERNOON
IN TWO TONIGHT AND THROUGH
EARLY TOMORROW MORNING.
A WINTER STORM WARNING FOR
GARRETT AND ALLEGHENY CAN ELSE.
YOUR ADVISORS FROM THE
IMMEDIATE METRO AREA.
A WALL WITHIN THE ACTION OF THE
NEXT-TO-LAST HOUR BUT NOW
FILLING IN WITH RAIN THROUGH
ARLINGTON OVER THROUGH TYSONS
BUT WE STILL HAVE A BIT OF THE
WINTRY MIX IT SNOW UP TO
FREDERICK AND WE ARE NOT
LOOKING AT ANY ADDITIONAL
COMMISSIONS TO THE NORTH, AT
LEAST NOT RIGHT NOW.
HERE IS TO THE BELTWAY IF YOU
ARE TRAVELING OVER THROUGH
ESTHER HARPER AREA AND LOOKING
AT WHAT ROADWAYS EMAIL TO SLOW
IT DOWN A BIT.
WITH MORE RAIN ON THE WAY WITH
THE EVENING RUSH HOUR COMMUTE.
TEMPERATURES ARE STILL WELL
ABOVE FREEZING AND 37 AT REAGAN
NATIONAL AIRPORT IN A LITTLE
BIT COLDER OFF TO THE WEST OF
US.
RIGHT AT THE FREEZING MARK FOR
WINCHESTER AND OVER INTO A.
HERE IS OUR HOURLY FORECAST IF
YOU ARE GRABBING A BITE FOR
LUNCH OR HAVE ANY OUTDOOR
ACTIVITIES PLAN.
MAKE SURE YOU HAVE AN UMBRELLA.
WE ARE NOT TALKING ABOUT HEAVY
RAIN BUT WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
POCKETS OF RAIN THAT WILL
CONTINUE TO THE AFTERNOON AND
INTO THE EVENING WITH
TEMPERATURES IN THE UPPER 30S.
TALKING ABOUT TONIGHT AND THE
POTENTIAL FOR SLICK SPOTS,
EARLY TOMORROW MORNING, BUT
THERE IS LIGHT AT THE END OF
THE TUNNEL.
WE HAVE MILDER TEMPERATURES ON
THE WAY IT WOULDN'T YOU KNOW
IT?
JUST IN TIME FOR VALENTINE'S
DAY.
MORE ON THAT IN A FEW MINUTES.
>>Adrianna: THANK YOU STEVE.
POLITICAL CHAOS CONTINUES TO
HAVE A HOLD ON THE
COMMONWEALTH.
THE BUSINESS OF STATE
GOVERNMENT CONTINUES.
AS POLITICAL FUTURES ARE STILL
UNCERTAIN, ALL EYES REMAIN ON
RICHMOND AND DOMICILES IS LIVE
FROM THE STATE CAPITAL WITH
THIS LATEST TWIST.
>>John: GOOD AFTERNOON AND TAKE
A LOOK AT THIS FRONT AND CENTER
ON THE RICHMOND TIMES DISPATCH
AND AT THIS HOUR, STATE
DELEGATES ARE FILING INTO THE
STATE CAPITAL HERE IN RICHMOND.
THE GENERAL ASSEMBLY WILL
CONVENE AT THIS HOUR, BUT THERE
WILL BE NO FILING FOR AN
IMPEACHMENT JUST YET.
>>> A SERIES OF SCANDALS
STARTED 10 DAYS AGO THAT SHOOK
THE STATE CAPITAL HERE IN
RICHMOND.
THE LATEST TREMOR HAS FIZZLED A
BIT, INITIALLY DEMOCRATIC
DELEGATE PATRICK HOPE SAID HE
WOULD BEGIN THE IMPEACHMENT
PROCESS AGAINST LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR JUSTIN FAIRFAX.
BUT NOW HOPE SAYS HE WANTS TO
WAIT IT OUT.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE, NOW, MORE
THAN ONE CREDIBLE ALLEGATION.
THE LAST ONE WHICH HAS BEEN
CORROBORATED AT THE TIME.
HE HAS TO RESIGN.
>> THE DELEGATE SAID HE
RECEIVED AN ENORMOUS AMOUNT OF
SINCERE AND THOUGHTFUL FEEDBACK
BUT ADDITIONAL COMPLETION IS
NEEDED TO TAKE PLACE BEFORE
ANYTHING IS FILED.
IN THE MEANTIME, JUSTIN FAIRFAX
IS URGING THE FBI TO LOOK INTO
THE BRIEF CLAIMS BY TWO
DIFFERENT WOMEN.
>> THEY COULD, IN THEORY, HAND
THE STATE WHICH HAD BEEN
TRENDING DEMOCRATIC BACK TO
REPUBLICANS FOR A LONG TIME.
>>John: THROUGH ATTORNEYS FOR
BOTH WOMEN, VANESSA TYSON AND
MEREDITH WATSON SAID THEY ARE
WILLING TO TESTIFY IF AN
IMPEACHMENT HEARING AND SO
MOVING FORWARD.
>> I BELIEVE BOTH WOMEN AND I
SEE NO REASON WHY PEOPLE COME
BEFORE BUT THERE'S NOTHING TO
GAIN, NO LAWSUIT OR MONEY
INVOLVED.
THESE WERE BOTH DOCUMENTS SOME
YEARS BACK IT WAS NOT CREATED
OVERNIGHT.
I BELIEVE THE WOMEN AND I THINK
IF YOU BELIEVE THE WOMEN THAT
WE HAVE NO CALL TO CALL FOR HIS
RESIGNATION.
>>John: DELICATE HOPE TO PUT
OUT AN OFFICIAL STATEMENT THIS
MORNING SAYING IN PART,
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR FAIRFAX
SHOULD HAVE ALREADY RESIGNED.
IT IS ATROCIOUS THAT HE WILL BE
PRESIDING OVER THE SENATE OF
VIRGINIA WITH THESE
ALLEGATIONS.
THE MESSAGE BEING SAID, HE
SAYS, TO THE VICTIM'S OF SEXUAL
ASSAULT IS CHILLING AND HE IS
RENEWING HIS CALL FOR FAIRFAX
TO RESIGN IMMEDIATELY.UT THE
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR VEHEMENTLY
DENIES ALL OF THE ALLEGATIONS.
REPORTING LIVE AT THE STATE
CAPITAL HERE IN RICHMOND, JOHN
GONZALEZ ABC7 NEWS.
>>Adrianna: ,RALPH NORTHAM
STRING OF MORE CONTROVERSY
DURING HIS FIRST TV INTERVIEW
SINCE ADMITTING TO INVITE FACE
AT A PARTY IN THE 80S BUT HE IS
NOW UNDER FIRE FOR HIS CHOICE
OF WORDS WHEN ADDRESSING THE
400 YEAR ANNIVERSARY OF THE
FIRST SLAVES BROUGHT TO
AMERICA.>> I KNOW THIS HAS
BEEN A VERY DIFFICULT WEEK FOR
YOU AND THE STATEOF VIRGINIA.
WHERE WOULD YOU LIKE TO BEGIN?
>> IT HAS BEEN A DIFFICULT WEEK
AND IF YOU LOOK AT VIRGINIA'S
HISTORY WE ARE NOW AT THE 400
YEAR ANNIVERSARY , JUST 90
MILES FROM HERE IN 1619 THE
FIRST INDENTURED SERVANTS FROM
AFRICA LANDED ON OUR SHORES AT
ALL POINT, COMFORT WHAT WE CALL
NOW FOR MONROE.
>> ALSO KNOWN AS SLAVERY.
>> YES.
>>Adrianna: A RECENT PLL FROM
THE "WASHINGTON POST" FOUND
THAT 47 PERCENT OF VIRGINIANS
ONE GOVERNOR NORTHAM TO STEP
DOWN.
BUT 47 PERCENT ALSO WANT HIM TO
STAY.
TO KEEP TRACK OF THE STORY AS
IT CHANGES DOWNLOAD THE FREE
ABC7 NEWS APP YOU CAN GET
ALERTS AND SWITCH YOUR PHONE.
MAKE NOW TO A POSSIBILITY OF
ANOTHER GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
THE TEMPORARY FUNDING MEASURES
THAT THE PRESIDENT SIGNED THAT
REOPENED THE GOVERNMENT RUNS
OUT OF FRIDAY AT MIDNIGHT.
NOW THEY ARE WORKING TO AVERT
ANOTHER SHUTDOWN BUT TALKS HAVE
STALLED WITH SERENA MARSHALL
WITH THE JEWS THEY COULD HAMMER
OUT A DEAL.
>>Reporter: DAYS AWAY FROM
ANOTHER SHUTDOWN AND
NEGOTIATIONS ARE STALLED.
>> I THINK THE BIG PROBLEM HERE
IS, THIS HAS BECOME AN EGO
NEGOTIATION AND THIS IS NOT
REALLY OVER SUBSTANCE.
>> THEY HOPE TO ANNOUNCE A DEAL
TODAY BUT THE STICKING POINT IS
NOT JUST OVER THE WALL ANYMORE.
>> THAT WE WERE TRACKING PRETTY
GOOD OVER THE LAST WEEK BUT IT
SEEMS OVER THE LAST 24 HOURS OR
SO THAT THE GOALPOST HAD BEEN
MOVING FROM THE DEMOCRATS.
>> DEMOCRATS NOT WANT ELEMENT
OF THE BEDS OF DETENTION
CENTERS.
REPUBLICANS WANT THE BEST
NUMBER TO GO UP AS PER YOUR
FUNDS DROPPED FROM THE PRESENT
STATEMENT OF $5.7 BILLION WITH
THE PRESENT RESPONDING ON
TWITTER.
WRITING, THE DEMOCRATS DO NOT
WANT US TO DETAIN OR SEND BACK
CRIMINAL ALIENS.
THIS IS A BRAND-NEW DEMAND.
CRAZY.
HIS ACTING CHIEF OF STAFF TOLD
FOX NEWS,
>> THE GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN
INSTANTLY STILL ON THE TABLE.
>> ALSO STILL ON THE TABLE IS A
NATIONAL THAT COULD -- NATIONAL
EMERGENCY DECLARATION.
HIS THE ROAD TO EL PASO, TEXAS.
THE CITY HE TOUTED DURING THE
STATE OF THE UNION AS.
>> IT USED TO HAVE EXTREMELY
HIGH RATES OF VIOLENT CRIME.
>> EL PASO OFFICIALS DENOUNCED
THAT CLAIM AND ACCORDING TO THE
EL PASO TIMES, THE CITY HAD THE
THIRD LOWEST VIOLENT CRIME RATE
AMONG COMPARABLE CITIES BEFORE
CONSTRUCTION BEGAN.> THERE
IS NO APPETITE FOR ANOTHER
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN BUT IT
STILL PUTS THE CHANCE OF IT
HAPPENING ANYWAY AT 50 PERCENT.
SERENA MARSHALL ABC NEWS
WASHINGTON.
>>Adrianna: ACTING DEFENSE
SECTOR IS NOW IN AFGHANISTAN.
THE UNANNOUNCED VISIT IS HIS
FIRST AND HE WILL MEET WITH
U.S. COMMANDERS AND AFGHAN
LEADERS.
SHANAHAN TOLD REPORTERS
TRAVELING WITH HIM THAT HIS
MESSAGE TO AFGHANS IS THAT THEY
MUST ULTIMATELY DECIDE THEIR
OWN FUTURE, INCLUDING HOW PEACE
IS TO BE ACHIEVED WITH THE
TALIBAN.
>>> A CONVICTED SEX OFFENDER IS
CHARGED WITH RAPING A WOMAN HE
MET AT CLYDE'S OF CHEVY CHASE.
POLICE SAY PHILIP KANTOR SAID
IT WOULD BE IN THE WOMAN'S
DRINK AT THE BAR LAST MONTH.
HE IS ACCUSED OF TAKING HER
BACK TO HIS APARTMENT WHERE HE
ATTACKED AND PHOTOGRAPHED HER.
THE WOMAN TOLD POLICE THAT SHE
HAS NO RELATION OF WHAT
HAPPENED FROM THE TIME SHE HAD
TO DRINK UNTIL SHE WOKE UP IN
HIS APARTMENT.
>>> NOW TO THE BLACKMAIL
ALLEGATIONS AGAINST JEFF BEZOS.
THEY APPARENTLY HAVE AN IDEA OF
WHO LEAKED HIS PRIVATE TEXT
MESSAGES AND PHOTOS.
MEANWHILE, IN AN EXCLUSIVE
INTERVIEW THE ATTORNEY FOR
NATIONAL ENQUIRER'S CHIEF
DENIES IT WAS ENGAGING IN
EXTORTION.
MAGGIE RULLI HAS THE LATEST.
>> THE BATTLE BETWEEN THE
WORLD'S RICHEST MAN, JEFF BEZOS
IN THE NATIONAL ENQUIRER
CONTINUES.
>> IT IS ABSOLUTE NOT EXTORTION
OR BLOOD.> THE ATTORNEY FOR
AMIS DETERMINED, THE COMMITTEE
WHO OWNS THE TABLET DENIED
ALLEGATIONS ON THIS WEEK AND
CLAIMS THE PERSON WHO LEAKED
INTIMATE TEXT MESSAGES BETWEEN
BASES AND HIS REPORTED
GIRLFRIEND HAS BEEN A RELIABLE
SOURCE FOR YEARS.
>> IT WAS A SOURCE THAT WAS
WELL-KNOWN TO BOTH MR. BASIS
AND MS. SANCHEZ.
>> ACCORDING TO THE DAILY PIECE
WITH ONE POSSIBLE SOURCE OF THE
LEAK TEXT IS SANCHEZ'S BROTHER,
A VOCAL SUPPORTER OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP.>> IF HE IS, I DO NOT
CONTROL THE POLITICAL ELEMENT
HERE.
>> MICHAEL DENIES THE
ALLEGATIONS.
>> HE CLAIMS THAT THE NATIONAL
ENQUIRER AND THE PARENT COMPANY
FRENCH RELEASE TEXT MESSAGES
AND PICTURES THAT THEY EXCHANGE
UNLESS BASES CALL ALL HIS
INVESTIGATION INTO HOW THEY GOT
THE PHOTOS AND RELEASED A
STATEMENT PUBLICLY DENIED THAT
THEIR PUBLICATION HAD ANY
POLITICAL MOTIVE.
>> THEY SEEM TO BE THE ONES WHO
ARE THE AGGRESSOR.
THEY SEEM TO BE DESPERATE TO
HAVE THIS POLITICAL ELEMENT
BEING RUDE REMOVED FROM THE
STRIP.
>> HOURS AFTER THE PLAYERS
POSE, JOURNALIST TWEETED TAT
WHILE HE WAS LOOK INTO THE
NATIONAL ENQUIRER'S
RELATIONSHIP WITH PRESIDENT
TRUMP, AMI URGED HIM TO STOP
DIGGING OR WE WILL ROUTE YOU.
HE SAYS HE DID NOT.
>> THIS SEEMS LIKE A PATTERN
PRACTICE ACCORDING TO THESE
JOURNALS.
>> I AM NOT AWARE OF ANY
ATTEMPT BY EMPLOYEES OF AMI TO
BLACKMAIL OR COMMIT ANY CRIME
AT ALL.
>> AMI HAS INSISTED ALL ALONG
THAT THEY HAVE OPERATED
LAWFULLY AND IN GOOD FAITH.
BUT THE BOARD IS INVESTIGATING
WITH MAGGIE RULLI ABC NEWS NEW
YORK.
>>Adrianna: COMING UP ON ABC7
NEWS AT NOON.
THEY MAYBE CUTE AND CUDDLY IN
THIS HOLIDAY COKE COMMERCIALS.
LIFE, POLAR BEARS ARE ANYTHING
BUT WARM AND COZY AND THEY ARE
CLOSING IN ON HUMANS.
SEE WHERE THEY HAVE INVADED IN
THE MEASURE BEING TAKEN TO KEEP
A COMMUNITY SAFE.
PLUS THE 61ST ACADEMY AWARDS IN
THE BOOKS.
THIS PRICE GUEST THAT KICKED
OFF THE SHOW.
>>Eric: LOOKING AT THE ROADWAYS
TODAY.SO FAR DESPITE
CONDITIONS OVERALL CONDITIONS
ARE NOT TOO BAD ON THE BIRDS.
IT IS NOT TOO SLICK OUT THERE.
TO WATCH OUT FOR THE CARS ON
FIVE SOUTHBOUND IN VIRGINIA
PAST FAIRFAX COUNTY PARKWAY.
THE TWO RIGHT LANES ARE STILL
BLOCKED OFF AT THIS POINT.
AN OVERTURNED ARMY TRANSPORT
VEHICLE AND THIS IS GOING TO BE
A BIT OF A COMPLICATED SPOT.
SOUTHBOUND TRAFFIC IS VERY
HEAVY APOSTASY AND HEADING DOWN
TO THE BELTWAY AS A RESULT.
TRY TO TAKE A LOOK AT SOME OF
THOSE DELAYS BACK TOWARD THE
SPRING FIELD E
People aren't talking
about how much money
they saved buying
Giant-brand chicken.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
At Giant, it's
the little things
that make mealtime easy,
so you have more time
with the people you love.
People aren't talking
about Giant's
fresh grab and go
salads and sandwiches.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
At Giant, it's
the little things
that make mealtime easy,
so you have more time
with the people you love.
>>Adrianna: HAPPENING RIGHT
NOW.
THOUSANDS OF TEACHERS IN DENVER
ARE HITTING THE PICKET LINES
INSTEAD OF HEADING TO CLASS.
THEIR START COMING AFTER TALKS
OF INCREASED SALARY AND BONUSES
WITH PUBLIC SCHOOLS FELL
THROUGH.
CLASSROOMS WILL BE STAFFED BY
DEMONSTRATORS AND SUBSTITUTES.
THE STRIKE SNEERINGLY DISRUPTS
DAY-TO-DAY OPERATIONS AT 207
SCHOOLS WITH 90,000 STUDENTS.
TEACHERS ARE STRUGGLING TO MAKE
ENDS MEET AS THE COST OF LIVING
RISES.
>>> THERE IS AN INVASION
HAPPENING ON A RUSSIA ISLAND BY
POLAR BEARS.
TAKE A LOOK HERE.
STATE OF EMERGENCY HAS BEEN
DECLARED ON A REMOTE ISLAND OFF
OF RUSSIA SCARES BUT THIS AFTER
52 POLAR BEARS WERE SPOTTED
BETWEEN DECEMBER AND FEBRUARY.
A LOT OF THEM LOOKING FOR FOOD
AND FEEDING ON TRASH.
LOCALS HAVE REPORTED SEVERAL
ATTACKS.
THE CONTACT WITH HUMANS HAS
INCREASED AS CLIMATE CHANGE HAS
REDUCED THEIR CIS HABITATS.
SPECIALIST HAS BEEN DEPLOYED TO
SEDATE AND REMOVE MANY OF THOSE
POLAR BEARS.
>>> IS COMING IN ALL TOO OFTEN
OCCURS AT NBA GAMES.
BATS FLYING INTO ARENAS BUT THE
LATEST INCIDENT IS CAUSING A
HEALTH SCARE.
LOOSE BUT FORCING A BRIEF DELAY
DURING THE PACERS CLIPPERS GAME
INDIANA ANIMAL GETTING AWFULLY
CLOSE TO PEOPLE ON THE COURT
AND IN THE STANDS.
HEALTH OFFICIALS TELLING PEOPLE
WHO HAD CONTACT WITH THE BACK
THAT THEY MAY HAVE BEEN EXPOSED
TO BABIES.
JUST LAST MONTH THERE WERE TWO
BACK INCDENTS AT SPURS GAMES
IN SAN ANTONIO.
MAKE IT WAS MUSIC'S PIGMENT AT
THIS IS THE FIRST GRAMMY AWARDS
AND EQUIPMENT AND WRAP ARTIST
OPTION FIGURES BUT LAST NIGHT
BOTH TOOK CENTER STAGE WITH
HISTORIC WINS.
RICK HAS MORE FROM HOLLYWOOD.
>> THIS IS LOVE.
THIS IS LIFE.
THIS IS LIVING.
THIS IS WHITE IN ALL BECAUSE OF
MUSIC.
>> AFTER LAST YEAR'S GRAMMY
AWARDS WERE TAGGED GRAMMY'S SO
MEAL BY THE USE OF SOCIAL
MEDIA.
THE 61ST SCRIMMAGE RESPONDED.
TURNING IT INTO A NED PERME
ABOUT WOMEN.
>> MUSIC SHOWS US THAT ALL OF
IT MATTERS.
EVERY STORY, WITHIN EVERY VOIC
, EVERY NOTE WITHIN EVERY SONG.
>> THE THEME CARRY OVER TO
TRIBUTES TO DOLLY PARTON.
AND DIANA ROSS.
[MUSIC]
>> IT WAS ALSO REFLECTED BY
MANY OF THE BIG WINNERS WITH
SINGER-SONGWRITER BRANDI
CARLISLE ONE THREE AWARDS WHILE
SHE WAS BEST NEW ARTIST.
>> LADY GAGA ONE THREE GRAMS
INCLUDING ONE FOR SHALLOW FROM
A STAR IS BORN.
>> THIS IS AMERICA!
>> TWO ARTIST TIED FOR THE MOST
WORDS WITH FOR EACH.
CHILDERS GAMBINO WAS NOT ON
HAND TO ACCEPT TO ORGANIZE
BIGGEST AWARDS, RECORD AND SONG
OF THE YEAR.
>>
[MUSIC]
>> COUNTRY SINGER CASEY
MUSGRAVE WHO WAS IN ATTENDANCE
ALSO TO COME FOR AWARDS
INCLUDING ALBUM OF THE YEAR.
SUMMING UP THE NIGHT IN THE
INDUSTRY.
>> I WOULD HAVE NOTHING WITHOUT
SONGS, TO ME IT IS ALL ABOUT
THE SONGS.
>> IN HOLLYWOOD I AM RICK.
[MUSIC]
>>Adrianna: I MEAN, YOU WANT TO
SEE TALENT AND THERE IT IS.
GRAMMY'S POST ALICIA KEYS
PLAYING TWO BEAMS AT THE SAME
TIME DURING A TRIBUTE TO MANY
OF HER FAVORITE ARTISTS.
SHE PLAYED SONGS FROM LAUREN
HILL ALL THE WAY TO NOT KING
COLE.
KEYS MILLIE SAID SOCIAL MEDIA
ON FIRE AND IT WAS THE MOST
TALKED ABOUT DURING THE AWARD
SHOW.
SHE IS GOOD AND THAT IS WHAT
SHE DOES.
>>Steve: TALK ABOUT THINGS YOU
CAN LEARN TO DO.
BUT THEN THERE ARE OTHER THINGS
THAT ARE JUST NATURAL TALENT.
>>Adrianna: IN EIGHT.
>>Steve: THAT.
IT IS NATURAL TALENT.
>>Adrianna: SHE CAN PULL IT
OFF.
>>Steve: MY GOODNESS.
>>Adrianna: DID YOU WATCH?
YOU LIKE THE GRAMMYS.
>>Steve: HONESTLY, I DID NOT
KNOW A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE UNTIL
I HEARD THEIR SONGS.
GO FIGURE ON THAT ONE.
IT WAS A GOOD SHOW AND DIANA
ROSS 75 YEARS OLD AND LIVING
LIKE THAT AND LOOKING LIKE
THAT.
TWO THUMBS UP ON THAT ONE.
>>> TODAY IS NOT A TWO THUMBS
UP KIND OF DAY UNLESS YOU LIKE
A CLOUDY, DAMP AND COOL.
HAGERSTON HAD SNOW ON THE
GROUND SO THEY HAD SCHOOL
CANCELLATIONS AND DELAYS.
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE UP
THERE RIGHT NOW THE WINTER
WEATHER ADVISORY THROUGH THIS
AFTERNOON AND THROUGH THE
OVERNIGHT IN TOMORROW MORNING.
NO ACTIVE ADVISORY OVER A
NATURAL HARBOR OVERLOOKING
TOWARD THE WILSON BRIDGE AND
OLD TOWN ALEXANDRIA AT REAGAN
NATIONAL AIRPORT.
CHECK WITH YOUR AIR CARRIER AND
YOU MIGHT FIND A FEW DELAYS AS
ADMITTED TO THE AFTERNOON
BECAUSE OF THE WEATHER.
37 DEGREES AT THE AIRPORT AT
THIS HOUR AND WE STAYED AT 35
IN MANASSAS.
STILL AT THE FREEZING MARK IN
WINCHESTER AND LEESBURG AND 33
IN GAITHERSBURG, AND IS NOW AT
34 DEGREES BUT STORM WATCH 7
SATELLITE AND RADAR IF YOU ARE
LIVING INSIDE THE BELTWAY OR
AROUND THE BELTWAY, BUT WHETHER
DOES CONTINUE.
HEAD OVER TOWARD FREDERICK AND
UP TOWARDS HAGERSTOWN AND A
LITTLE BIT OF LIGHT SNOW AT
THIS TIME.
A LOT OF IT HAVING A HARD TIME
REACHING THE GROUND BUT WE HAVE
RAIN DROPS FALLING FROM THE SKY
RIGHT NOW OVER TOWARD TYSON IN
SILVER SPRING, COLLEGE PARK AND
ALSO DOWN TOWARD OLD TOWN.
AS WE HEAD TO THE AFTERNOON
HOURS WE WILL LOOK FOR AREAS OF
RAIN THAT WILL CONTINUE ALONG
WITH THE WINTRY MIX OFF TOWARD
THE NORTH AND WEST WITH THE
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY DOES
CONTINUE AT THIS TIME TO THE
OVERNIGHT.
PULL OFF TO THE WEST WE ARE
TALKING OFF TO THE NORTH AND
WAS, WINTER STORM WARNINGS FOR
GARRETT AND ALLEGHENY COUNTIES
AND THAT CONTINUES UNTIL 12:00.
WE ALSO HAVE A WINTER STORM
WATCH THE WILL EITHER AGREE TO
AN ADVISOR OR WARNING FOR
MARTINSBURG IN WINCHESTER IN
THE SAME FOR ROMNEY.
HERE IS OUR UPDATED FUTURECAST.
YES, BUT WHETHER DOES CONTINUE
AND WILL BECOME A LITTLE BIT
LATER ON THIS AFTERNOON BUT
WILL PICK UP AGAIN ESPECIALLY
NORTH AND WEST OF TOWN MOVING
TO THE AFTERNOON HOURS INTO THE
EVENING AND OVERNIGHT.
BY EARLY TOMORROW MORNING WE
COULD BE LOOKING AT A BIT OF
WINTRY MIX AND SLEET OFF TOWARD
THE NORTH AND WEST.AS ALL OF
THIS CHANGES OVER TO ALL RAIN
TOMORROW AND WE COULD BE
LOOKING AT A TOTAL OF INCH OF
RAIN BY THE TIME THE SYSTEM
MOVES OUT OF FEAR.
FOR TODAY, KEEP AN UMBRELLA
HANDY IN THE UPPER 30S AND
DINING OUT TONIGHT, WALKING ON
14TH STREET LOOKING AT
TEMPERATURES IN THE MIDDLE TO
UPPER 30S WITH ON AND OFF
SHOWERS TO CONTINUE.
NIGHTTIME LOWS WILL RANGE FROM
32 TO 37 DEGREES.
EARLY TOMORROW MORNING, BE ON
THE LOOKOUT FOR SLICK SPOTS,
ESPECIALLY NORTH AND WEST OF
TOWN.
HOUR BY HOUR FORECAST FOR
TOMORROW DOES SHOW MODERATE
TEMPERATURES.
THEY WILL BE IN THE MIDDLE 40S
FOR DAYTIME HIGHS AND GRABBED
THE UMBRELLA AND YOU WILL NEED
IT.
MODERATE RAIN DURING THE
AFTERNOON THERE WILL CLEAR
THINGS UP.
WHEN YOU KNOW IT?
FOR THE MIDDLE OF THE WEEK 47
ON WEDNESDAY IN VALENTINE'S DAY
IN THE MIDDLE 50S BUT LO
>>Adrianna: WE ARE BACK NOW
WITH THE NEW TWIST BETWEEN THE
FIJI WATER IN THE COMPANY HE
MADE HER FAMOUS.
TJ HOLMES HAS THE DETAILS.
>> SHE IS THE MODEL THAT
LAUNCHED A THOUSAND MEANS.
KELLY STEINBOCK, THE FIJI WATER
GIRL.
SHE PHOTOBOMB HER WAY OUT OF
OBSCURITY AT THIS YEAR'S GOLDEN
GLOBES BY POSING WITH BOTTLES
OF WATER BETWEEN EVERY STAR
THAT SHE COULD FIND WITH HIS IS
BEHIND NICOLE KIDMAN AND HERE
SHE IS AGAIN BETWEEN RICHARD
MADDEN.
HER INSTANT INTERNET FAME ALSO
ENTER AN APPEARANCE IN
LATE-NIGHT.
>> ARE YOU THE GIRL FROM LAST
NIGHT?
>> THAT IS ME.
>> NOW FIJI SAYS HER 15 MINUTES
ARE UP.
THEY FILED A LAWSUIT AGAINST
HER CLAIMING THAT SHE RENEGED
ON A DEAL TO BE A BRAND
AMBASSADOR FOR FIJI.
THERE SHOULD THEY ACCUSE HER OF
TRYING TO CAPITALIZE ON HER
FLEETING 15 MINUTES OF INTERNET
FAME AND EXTORT FIJI BECAUSE
SHE WANTED A BETTER DEAL THAN
THE ORIGINAL $90,000 SHE HAD
ORIGINALLY ACCEPTED.
THE COMPANY'S LAWSUIT IS A
COUNTER TO A LAWSUIT THAT SHE
FILED LAST MONTH.
SHE SUED BG AND ITS PARENT
COMPANY, THEWONDERFUL COMPANY,
FOR NEARLY HALF A MILLION
SAYING THAT THE COMPANIES WERE
TRYING TO CAPITALIZE ON HER
OVERNIGHT FAME , USED HER LIKE
THIS WITHOUT HER PERMISSION TO
CREATE A WORLDWIDE CARDBOARD
CUTOUT MARKETING CAMPAIGN.
>>Adrianna: WHEN WILL WE SEE
SANTA AGAIN?
>>Steve: WEDNESDAY.
HERE WE ARE ON MONDAY THAT IS
48 HOURS AWAY.
HIGH TEMPERATURE TODAY ONLY IN
THE HIGH-40S BUT WE HAVE
TOMORROW ANOTHER RAINY DAY.
IT WILL BE A SLOW GO FOR THE
EARLY MORNING, OR SHOULD SAY
MORE COMMITTED THE MANDATE INTO
THE EVENING AND THEN DISCUSS
WILL BEGIN TO CLEAR IT LITTLE
ON THE WINDY SKY WEDNESDAY AND
VALENTINE'S DAY INTO THE 50S IN
THE NICOLE FRONT ON FRIDAY.
THAT WILL DROP OUT OF RESPECT
DOWN INTO THE 40S.
A WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY FOR
FREDERICK COUNTY AND WASHINGTON
COUNTIES AND IN MARYLAND AND
THAT IS THROUGH TOMORROW
MORNING.
NOT THE BEST OUT THERE BUT IT
IS NOT IMPORTANT AT LEAST AND
THAT IS GOOD.
BE PREPARED IF YOU ARE DRIVING
UP SUNDAY TO
>> YOU ARE WATCHING ABC7 NEWS
AT NOON.
ON YOUR SIDE.
>>Adrianna: YOU KNOW IT IS A
SLOPPY DAY WHEN THE TRACTION ON
YOUR BOOTS IS AS HANDY AS WHAT
IS ON YOUR TIRES.
WE ARE IN FREDERICK WITH A LOOK
AT THE ICE CONDITIONS FOR THOSE
WHO HAD A HEAD OUT EARLY THIS
MORNING.
>> WINTER IS BACK THIS TIME A
MIX OF SLEET AND FREEZING RAIN
HAS US SLIDING INTO THE WEEK.
>> ARE THE SIDEWALK SLIPPERY?
>> NOT ANYMORE.
THEY WERE.
THERE WAS LIKE THAT MUCH ICE.
>> IT IS A DAY WHEN YOUR BOOTS
NEED AS MUCH TRACTION AS YOUR
TIRES PUT.
>> THANK YOU BE A LITTLE BIT
MORE DANGEROUS AND CONSTANT
DRIVING.
WE DO A GOOD JOB TRYING TO
MAINTAIN THE SIDEWALKS BUT
SOMETIMES IT COMES UPON US
QUICKLY DOWN HERE.
>> DOUGLAS HENDERSON HAD TO GET
OUT EARLY TO SHOVEL THE
SIDEWALKS, LINK ICE MELT FIRST
HELPED HIM CLEAR THEM OUT
QUICKLY.
p>> IT IS LIKE BLACK ICE BUT IT
LOOKS WET BUT IT IS SLIPPERY.
>> TAKE A LOOK AT THE SIDEWALKS
NEAR LINCOLN ELEMENTARY IN
DOWNTOWN FREDERICK.
COUNTY SCHOOLS WERE ON A
TWO-HOUR DELAY BEFORE
ADMINISTRATORS TOOK ANOTHER
LOOK AND DECIDED TO CLOSE.
>> WE TOOK STORM TRACK 72 AREAS
NORTH AND WEST OF THE CITY AND
THAT IS WHAT WE NOTICED SLUSHY
ROADS AND ICY SIDEWALKS.
THE MAIN ROADS WERE MRS. --
MOSTLY WHITE.
>> AROUND 5:30 A.M. WE SPOTTED
A BUNCH OF SALT TRUCKS ON
INTERSTATE 70 GOING TO
WASHINGTON IN FREDERICK
COUNTIES. FRESH LAYER OF
SALT HELPED TO MELT THE ICE.
AS WE GET CLOSER TO VALENTINE'S
DAY, SO MANY ARE HOPING THAT
MOTHER NATURE SHOWS US SOME
LOVE.> I WOULD RATHER BE ONE
THING COLD.
>> IN FREDERICK, CHERYL
O'CONNOR ABC7 NEWS.
>>Adrianna: HERE IS A LIVE LOOK
AT I-95 NORTH IN FAIRFAX AND
YOU CAN SEE BAD TRAFFIC THERE.
LOOKS LIKE AN ACCIDENT OFF TO
THE SIDE OF THE ROAD THERE.
THOSE SLICK CONDITIONS CAN STAY
FOR A WHILE.
METEOROLOGIST STEVE RUDIN IS
HERE WITH A CHECK OF THE
FORECAST.
>>Steve: WE ARE LOOKING AT THE
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY FOR
FREDERICK AND WASHINGTON
COUNTIES IN MARYLAND.
OVERLOOKING THE PENTAGON AND
PENTAGON CITY WE HAVE BUT
ROADWAYS AND RAN ACROSS THE
AREA.
A COLBURN, IT DEFINITELY IS BUT
WE ARE LOOKING AT MORE WITH
WEATHER AT GARRETT AND
ALLEGHENY COUNTIES IN WESTERN
MARYLAND.
IF YOUR TRAVELS TAKE YOU THAT
DIRECTION TODAY OVER TOWARD
CUMBERLAND AND FROSTBURG YOU
WANT TO LEAVE MORE TIME.ERE
IS SUNLIGHT SEVEN RADAR.
HEADED TOWARD FREDERICK AND
VERMONT AND PRINCIPAL IN
HAGERSTOWN AND THAT IS WHERE WE
HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF SLEET
MIXED IN WITH THE RAIN AT THIS
HOUR.
ONCE AGAIN, TRAVELING FROM
TYSONS TOWARD SILVER SPRING,
COLLEGE PARK, LOOKING AT WHAT
ROADWAYS BUT IT MIGHT SLOW YOU
DOWN A BIT MOVING TO THE
AFTERNOON HOURS.
TEMPERATURES ARE ABOVE FREEZING
AT REAGAN NATIONAL AIRPORT AND
MOVING THROUGH THIS AFTERNOON
KEEP AN UMBRELLA HEAVY, LEAVE
EXTRA TIME.
UPPER 30S FOR DAYTIME HIGHS.
TALKING ABOUT A MILDER DAY
TOMORROW BUT IT IS GOING TO BE
A BUT ONE AROUND THE DMV.
WE DO HAVE CLEARING SKIES ON
THE WAY AND I WILL SHOW YOU THE
FRESHLY UPDATED SUNDAY OUTLOOK
COMING UP IN A FEW MINUTES.
>>Adrianna: NOW TO THE LATEST
OUT OF IRGINIA.
GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM SPEAKING
OUT ABOUT THE POLITICAL CHAOS
THAT HAS GRIPPED HIS STATE AND
THE FUTURE.
WE CONTINUE OUR TEAM COVERAGE
FROM RICHMOND.
>> VIRGINIA'S GOVERNOR RALPH
NORTHAM BREAKING HIS SILENCE IN
REFUSING CALLS TO RESIGN, BUT
ADMITTING THAT HE THOUGHT ABOUT
LEAVING OFFICE.
>> YES, I HAVE THOUGHT ABOUT
RESIGNING, BUT I HAVE ALSO
THOUGHT ABOUT WHAT VIRGINIA
NEEDS RIGHT NOW.
I REALLY FEEL LIKE I AM IN A
POSITION WHERE I CAN TAKE
CONTINUE TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
>> CRITICS SAY, EVEN IN HIS
FIRST TV INTERVIEW SINCE THE
SCANDAL BROUGHT WITH HIM AND HE
STILL SOUNDS OUT OF TOUCH.
>> JUST 90 MILES FROM HERE AND
IN 1619, THE FIRST INDENTURED
SERVANTS FROM AFRICA LANDED ON
OUR SHORES AT OPEN COMFORT, BUT
WE CALL NOW FORT MONROE.
>> ALSO KNOWN AS SLAVERY.
>> YES.
WHILE WE HAVE MADE A LOT OF
PROGRESS IN VIRGINIA, SLAVERY
HAS ENDED, SCHOOLS HAVE BEEN
DESEGREGATED WE HAVE AND THE
JIM CROW LAWS.
EASIER ACCESS TO VOTING.
IT IS ABUNDANTLY CLEAR THAT WE
STILL HAVE A LOT OF WORK TO DO.
>> HIS PROBLEMS START.
THIS RAISES FEDERAL FROM HIS
MEDICAL SCHOOL FACEBOOK PAGE.
HE DID ADMIT TO APPEARING ONCE
IN BLACK ICE BUT SAYS HE IS NOT
ONE OF THOSE TWO MEN.
>> COMPLICATING THE MATTER IS,
VIRGINIA'S LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR
JUSTIN FAIRFAX HAS NOW BEEN
ACCUSED OF TWO WOMEN OF SEXUAL
ASSAULT, WHICH HE NOW DENIES
POLITICAL SCIENCE PROFESSOR
VANESSA TYSON SAID HE FORCED
HER TO PERFORM A SEX ACT IN
2004.
MEREDITH WATSON SAYS FAIRFAX
SEXUALLY ASSAULTED HER WHILE
BOTH WERE STUDENTS AT DUKE
UNIVERSITY IN 2000.> IF
THESE TRANSITIONS ARE
DETERMINED TO BE TRUE I DO NOT
THINK HE WILL HAVE ANY OTHER
OPTION BUT TO RESIGN.
>> OTHERS ARE DONE GIVING
FAIRFAX ANYMORE CHANCES,
INCLUDING FELLOW DEMOCRATS.
>> HE NEEDS TO RESIGN
IMMEDIATELY.SHOULD THE
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR FAILED TO
DO SO, ON MONDAY I INTEND TO
INTRODUCE ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENT ON LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR JUSTIN FAIRFAX.
>>Adrianna: ATTORNEYS FOR BOTH
WOMEN, MEREDITH WATSON AND
VANESSA TYSON SAID THEY ARE
WILLING TO TESTIFY IF AN
IMPEACHMENT HEARING MOVES
FORWARD FAIRFAX HAS VEHEMENTLY
DENIED BOTH ALLEGATIONS AND
ASKING FOR DUE PROCESS AND ALSO
ASKING THAT NO ONE RUSH TO
JUDGMENT.
MAKE A NEW PULL FROM THE
"WASHINGTON POST" SHOWS JUST
HOW DIVIDED BETWEEN IS ON THIS
POLITICAL SCANDAL.
47 PERCENT OF RESIDENTS WANTED
GOVERNOR NORTHAM TO STAND DOWN
AND 47 PERCENT BUT HIM TO STAY
IN OFFICE.
EXPERTS SAY THAT MIGHT MAKE IT
A CHALLENGE FOR THE GOVERNOR TO
GET THINGS DONE FOR THE REST OF
HIS TERM.
>> THE GOVERNOR WAS THINKING
VERY SERIOUSLY ABOUT WHETHER HE
COULD BE EFFECTIVE IN THE ROLE
AS GOVERNOR.
AND YET, THE SURVEY DATA SHOWED
THAT THE CORE OF THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY AND ALSO
AFRICAN-AMERICANS IN THE STATE
ARE SUPPORTING HIM TO STAY IN
OFFICE.
>>Adrianna: DESPITE THOSE
POCKETS OF SUPPORT, 7/10
VIRGINIANS SAY THE GOVERNOR
STATEMENT ABOUT THE RACIST
YEARBOOK PHOTO ARE NOT
BELIEVABLE AND OTHERS SAY HE
WILL BE EFFECTIVE FOR THE THREE
YEARS LEFT IN HIS TERM.
>>> NOW TO AN ABC NEWS
EXCLUSIVE.
NEVER BEFORE HEARD AUDIOTAPES
OF ADMISSION THE COMMITTEE
ADMITTED RUSSIA.
>> IT IS VERY HARD.T IS SO
MUCH PAIN.
>> YOU ARE LISTENING TO THE
VOICE OF MARIA BUTINA, THE GUN
CLUB AND GRADUATE STUDENT AND
RUSSIAN NATIONAL ACCUSED OF
COURTING CONSERVATIVE ELITE AND
POWER PLAYERS IN THE NRA ON
BEHALF OF THE KREMLIN.
THIS MORNING WE ARE HEARING THE
30-YEAR-OLD SPEAK FOR THE FIRST
TIME SINCE HER JULY ARREST.
DEFENDING HERSELF AGAINST
ALLEGATIONS THAT SHE WAS
WORKING AS A COVERT FORD AGENT.
>> YOU WOULD NEVER SEE ME IN
PUBLIC.
I WOULD BE THE MOST UNSEEN
PERSON ON EARTH.
>> SHE RECORDED THIS DUET WITH
AN NRA INSIDER AFTER THEY
BECAME ROMANTICALLY INVOLVED.
SHE SPENT TIME WITH AUTHOR AND
JOURNALIST JIM BELFORD DURING
THE LAST MONTHS OF HER FREEDOM.
BAMFORD RECORDING THEIR
CONVERSATIONS FOR A PIECE IN
THE LATEST ISSUE OF THE NEW
REPUBLIC TITLE, THE SPY WHO
WASN'T.
>> WE HAVE HAD A NUMBER OF LONG
INTERVIEWS, BUT ONE TIME SHE
JUST NEVER SHOWED UP.
THE NEXT DAY SHE APOLOGIZED AND
SHE SAID THE FBI HAD RATED HER
APARTMENT.
>> WAS THERE POUNDING ON THE
DOOR?
DID THEY HEAL FBI?
>> YES THEY SAID THEY HAD A
SEARCH WARRANT.
THEY PUSHED ME IN.
>> A PAMPERED CHEF IS NEVER
BEFORE SEEN PHOTOS TAKEN IN THE
AFTERMATH OF THE RAID.
>> SHE WAS REALLY FRIGHTENED BY
IT ALL.
>> AFTER SHE WAS ARRESTED, HER
CONVERSATIONS WITH HIM
CONTINUED FROM BEHIND BARS.
>> I EXERCISE AND I READ IN A
SLEEP.
I AM ONLINE FOR 22 HOURS A GOOD
TWO HOURS AT NIGHT TO DO
EVERYTHING.
>> IN DECEMBER SHE CUT A DEAL
WITH FEDERAL PROSECUTORS,
PLEADING GUILTY TO CONSPIRACY
TO ACT AS A FOREIGN AGENT.UT
HE BELIEVES THAT SHE IS JUST
LOOKING FOR A WAY OUT.
>> THINK SHE IS PROBABLY HOPING
THAT THIS MAY BRING AN END TO
IT AND SHE WILL GO BACK TO
RUSSIA IN THIS WILL BE A
NIGHTMARE THAT IS OVER.
>>Adrianna: PROSECUTORS SAY SHE
IS COOPERATING WITH THEM BUT
SAYS SHE IS A FLIGHT RISK.
MEANWHILE, SHE CLAIMS SHE WAS
NEVER INTERVIEWED BY SPECIAL
COUNSEL ROBERT MUELLER'S
OFFICE.
AS PART OF THE INVESTIGATION
INTO RUSSIAN ELECTION MEDDLING.
>>> MANY OF US KNOW THAT BIG
BROTHER IS ALWAYS WATCHING BUT
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN WHAT HE SEES
GETS SHARED WITH PEOPLE WHO
MAKE IMPORTANT DECISIONS ABOUT
OUR FUTURE?
IT IS ALREADY HAPPENING IN
CHINA AND AS OUR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT KRISTINE FRAZAO
REPORTS, SOMETHING THE U.S.
COULD BE NEXT.
>> FROM WHAT WE EAT TO WHERE WE
GO TO WHO OUR FRIENDS ARE.
THE DATA COLLECTED ON EACH OF
US IS EXPANSIVE SAYS FORMER
SECRETARY OF HOMELAND SECURITY.
>> THEY KNOW WHO YOUR FRIENDS
ARE, WHAT YOUR FRIENDS DO, BUT
YOU ARE DOING ONLINE.
NOW WE HAVE FACIAL RECOGNITION
THEY CAN TELL WHERE YOU ARE
GOING.
>> IN CHINA, INFORMATION LIKE
THIS IS USED TO GIVE EACH
PERSON, WHAT IS CALLED A SOCIAL
CREDIT SCORE.
FOR EVERY MOVE YOU MAKE IS
MONITORED AND SCORED.
IF YOUR SCORE GETS TOO LOW, YOU
MAYBE PREVENTED FROM GETTING A
JOB, TRAVELING BY AIR OR
HIGH-SPEED RAIL.T MAY EVEN
HURT YOUR CHILDREN'S CHANCES OF
GETTING INTO COLLEGE.
>> THE PROGRAM IS CURRENTLY
BEING TESTED IN CHINA WITH AN
OFFICIAL WILL UPDATE OF 2020.
FOR THE PURPOSE OF QUOTE,
CARING FOR SINCERITY AND
TRADITIONAL VIRTUES.
USING ENCOURAGEMENT TO KEEP
TRUST AND CONSTRAINTS AGAINST
BREAKING TRUST AS INCENTIVE
MECHANISMS.
HE NOW RUNS THE CONSULTING
COMPANY SAYS THERE ARE ALREADY
CLAIMS OF SOCIAL SCORING HERE
IN THE UNITED STATES.
>> WE ARE BEGINNING TO SEE IT
ALREADY.
INSURANCE COMPANIES AFFECT YOUR
PREMIUM BASED ON WHETHER YOU
ARE EATING HEALTHY, GETTING A
GOOD NIGHT SLEEP AND EXERCISE.
>> SAYS THE NEED FOR CONGRESS
TO ACT IS URGENT BUT THE
EMPHASIS NEEDS TO CHANGE FROM
HOW DO WE KEEP THINGS
CONFIDENTIAL, BECAUSE FRIENDLY
FOR MANY OF US, IT IS TOO LATE
FOR THAT.
INSTEAD PASS LAWS ON WHO
CONTROLS THE DATA ONCE IT HAS
BEEN GENERATED.
IN WASHINGTON I AM KRISTINE
FRAZAO.
>>Adrianna: COMING UP ON ABC7
NEWS AT NOON.
WE SHOWED YOU THE STATE
>>Adrianna: BACK NOW WITH THE
GLITZ AND GLAMOUR OF THE GRAMMY
AWARDS.
CAUGHT UP WITH THE BIGGEST
NOMINEES ON THE RED CARPET.
>> MUSIC BIGGEST NIGHT
SPONSORED SOME OF THE BREAD
CARPETS MRS. LING AND THE
SURPRISING FASHION.ITH
CARDIAC BE IN THE CENTERPIECE.
IT TOOK THE RED CARPET BY
STORM.
DRAWING COMPARISONS TO
BOTTICELLI'S VENUS AND THE
LITTLE MERMAID IS URSULA.
KENNY PERRY IN PINK MAKING FUN
OF THE MEANS BY POSTING THEM ON
HER INSTAGRAM.
AND JAYLA ROCKING THIS HAD
POSTED WITH LADY GAGA.
IT WAS A RED CARPET TO
REMEMBER.
OUR CAMERAS WERE THERE.E HAD
A ONE ON ONE WITH CASEY
MUSGRAVE JUST AFTER SHE WON THE
BEST COUNTRY SONG.
>> THAT IS SO BALD TO ME
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE WHEN ALL OF
THIS GOES AWAY, IT IS ALL ABOUT
THE SONGS BUT IT ALL STARTED
BECAUSE OF THE SONGS BUT I
WOULD NOT HAVE ANYTHING WITHOUT
SONG.
>> IN ALL SHE TO COME FOUR
GRAMS INCLUDING ALBUM OF THE
YEAR.
>> THIS IS IT!
OH MY GOSH!
I AM EXCITED.
>> THE GRAMMY GOES TO, GOLDEN
HOUR CASEY MUSGRAVE!
>> THE MOST TREATED MOMENT OF
THE NIGHT IS WHEN A POP
SUPERGROUP BTS TOOK THE STAGE
FOR THE FIRST TIME TO PRESENT
BEST OR IN THE ALBUM, TELLING
ME THIS ON THE RED CARPET.
>> TO ALL OUR FANS, THANK YOU
FOR MAKING THIS DREAM COME
TRUE.
>> K POP GROUP AND MOST POPULAR
BOY BAND IN THE WORLD, CALLED
MULTIPLE TIMES SING-ALONG WITH
MILEY CYRUS AND DOLLY PARTON.
>> BROTHERS OSBORNE TELLING ME
ON THE RED CARPET HOW EVERYONE
HERE TELLS -- FEELS ABOUT
DOLLY.
>> YOU HAVE GOT TO SEE DOLLY.
I ALWAYS THINK THE BEST ARTISTS
ARE REALLY JOURNALISTS AND SHE
IS.
SHE FITS IN THE CATEGORY OF
COUNTRY MUSIC, BUT WHO DOES NOT
THINK DOLLY PARTON SCHOOL?
EVERYBODY LOVES DOLLY.
>> I WANT TO BE DOLLY.
>> THE ALWAYS COOL BACKSTREET
BOYS NOMINATED FOR THE EIGHTH
TIME.
THEY DID NOT TAKE HOME ANY
AWARDS BUT WITH A NUMBER ONE
ALBUM IN THE BOOK RIGHT NOW, I
WOULD SAY THEY ARE STILL
WINNING.
>> WHAT YOU THINK IS THE SECRET
COMING TO COME BACK WHEN YOU
NEVER REALLY LEFT BUT IT IS
LIKE YOU RESEARCHED AND CAME
THIS FORCE THAT IS UNSTOPPABLE.
>> PERSEVERANCE IN WORKING
HARD.
NOT GIVING UP.
>> CHEMISTRY, PASSION.OVE.
WE LOVE WHAT WE DO.
>> THE LOVE FOR ONE ANOTHER AS
WELL.
AND OUR FANS.
>>Adrianna: DOES THAT MAKE YOU
FEEL OLD?
BACKSTREET BOYS?
>>Steve: THEY ARE LIKE MY AGE.
>>> THE WEATHER TODAY'S LITTLE
BIT ON THE GLOOMY SIDE AND
TOMORROW ANOTHER WHAT DAY ON
THE WAY.
WE HAVE BETTER WEATHER ON THE
WAY LATER ON THIS WEEK.ET
THE WORST OF IT OVER WITH NOW
AND THEN WE ENJOY THE REST OF
THE WEEK.
OVERLY NATIONAL CATHEDRAL FROM
OUR CAMERA WE HAVE READ ACROSS
THE AREA AND THE BEACHES
LOOKING AT RAINDROPS AT THIS
ARE NOT THE REAL ESTATE BUT
BEING BY THE OCEAN SOUNDS NICE.
REAGAN NATIONAL AIRPORT WITH A
LITTLE BIT OF FALLING OUT
THERE.
IF YOU ARE TRAVELING TODAY MAKE
SURE YOU LEAVE AN EXTRA FEW
MINUTES TO GET FROM POINT A TO
POINT B AS YOU MAY SLOW THINGS
DOWN BECAUSE OF THE WET
PAVEMENT.
ABOVE FREEZING IN DOWNTOWN D.C.
AND 32 DEGREES RIGHT AT THE
PRISON WORK IN LEESBURG IN THE
SAME OVER AT WINCHESTER, LORI
AND MAKING IT UP TO 34.
LOOKING AT 37 OVER AT ANNAPOLIS
AND READ THE FREEZING MARK AT
BWI MARSHALL.
STORM WATCH 7 SATELLITE AND
RADAR FILLING IN WITH PLENTY OF
RAIN INSIDE AND ON THE OUTSIDE
OF THE BELTWAY.
RAIN MAKES HIM A LITTLE BIT OF
SLEET AND SNOW.
WHEN TREATMENTS FOR FREDERICK
AND FAIRMONT AND OVER TOWARD
HAGERSTOWN.
THE WET ROADWAYS WILL STICK
AROUND, NOT ONLY FOR THIS
AFTERNOON BUT IN THE EVENING
RUSH HOUR COMMUTE.
AND THEN INTO THE OVERNIGHT.
ONCE AGAIN, LEAVE EXTRA TIME.
IF YOU HAVE THE LUXURY.
ALSO BE SURE TO NOTE THAT WE
HAVE WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY
NOT ONLY THROUGH THIS AFTERNOON
BUT INTO TONIGHT AND THEN INTO
EARLY TOMORROW MORNING.
FREDERICK COUNTY ALSO INTO
WASHINGTON COUNTY AND INCLUDES
HAGERSTOWN.
THEN THE WINTER STORM WARNING
FOR GARRETT AND ALLEGHENY
COUNTY IS OVER TOWARD
CUMBERLAND AND FROSTBURG.
THAT IS UNTIL NOON TOMORROW.
MR. MARCH FOR RALEIGH AND
WINCHESTER WILL LIKELY UPGRADE
TO PUT WEATHER ADVISORY AS WE
MOVE INTO THE OVERNIGHT HOURS
AND THEN EARLY TOMORROW
MORNING.
HERE IS THE FUTURECAST THAT HAS
JUST UPDATED FOR US.
HE DOES WANT TO KEEP BUT
WHETHER IN OUR FORECAST, THE
NORTHERN HALF OF THE CAPITAL
BELTWAY 4:00 THEN WE WILL HEAR
WINTRY MIX ALONG THE
MASON-DIXON LINE.
BY 8:00 P.M. TONIGHT.
THIS WILL ALSO BACK IN WITH
RAIN AND MODERATE TIMES, EARLY
TOMORROW MORNING AND THROUGH
THE AFTERNOON HOURS WITH 12
NOON, 24 HOURS FROM NOW AND WE
ARE STILL DEALING WITH WHAT
WEATHER AROUND THE DMV.
FINALLY WE GET THIS OUT OF HERE
LATELY TOMORROW NIGHT AND THEN
SKIES WILL BEGIN TO CLEAR BUT
IT WILL TURN WINDY FOR
WEDNESDAY.
SO, LUNCH TIME TODAY.
IF YOU ARE GOING TO BE OUT AND
ABOUT.
GRAB AN UMBRELLA AND LEAVE
EXTRA TIME AND WILL BE IN THE
UPPER 30S.
DINNERTIME HOUR IT WILL BE
TEMPERATURES IN THE UPPER 30S
WITH AREAS OF RAIN ONCE AGAIN.
NICE FLOW RATE FROM 32 TO 37
DEGREES WITH TEMPERATURES
AROUND THE FREEZING MARK AND
EVEN BELOW ON THE I-81 CORRIDOR
AND ALONG I-70. BE EXTRA
CAREFUL WITH WHAT SERVICES THAT
HAVE NOT BEEN TREATED AND THE
SLICK ROADWAYS ARE A
POSSIBILITY, EARLY TOMORROW
MORNING.
LISTEN TO WARM THINGS UP FROM
THE LOWER TO MIDDLE 40S WITH
HIGHS TOMORROW AND WILL BE ABLE
TO STAY WITH UPWARDS OF AN INCH
OF RAIN FOR THE TIME THE SYSTEM
FINALLY MOVES OUT OF HERE.
HERE'S A LOOK AT OUR FORECAST.
THE NEXT SEVEN DAYS.
43 TOMORROW AND 47 ON WEDNESDAY
AND VALENTINE'S DAY IN THE
MIDDLE 50S BUT AT LEAST IT WILL
BE DRY.
OUR NEXT BEST CHANCE FOR WHAT
>>Adrianna: EVEN IF YOU WANT TO
WORK OUT.
GETTING TO THE GYM CAN BE A
CHALLENGE BUT THAT IS WHY SOME
CLASSES WILL COME TO YOU.
WE CHECK OUT THIS TREND SEE DO
NOT WASTE YOUR MONEY.
>> THESE DAYS FOLKS IN THE D.C.
AREA STREAM EVERYTHING ON TVS
AND SMART PHONES BUT THE NEWEST
TREND IS STREAMING LIVE GYM
CLASSES AT HOME.
ONE COMPANY IS CASHING IN WITH
NEWCOMERS EVERY DAY.
THE IT IS BUT AS JANE FONDA IN
THE 90S RICHARD SIMMONS.
WITH THE MILLENNIUM CAME
KICKBOXING.
NOW IN 2019 THE HOTTEST WORKOUT
TREND IS A JAM STREAM TO YOUR
HOME.
DAVID IS IN A LIVE CLASS, NOT
AT THE GYM BUT AT HOME.
>> I DO NOT HAVE TO PACK A GYM
BAG OR A CHANGE OF CLOTHES BUT.
>> HE IS ONE OF THOUSANDS TO
JOIN THE PILOT ON WORKOUT
PROGRAM.
PROTON STREAMS LIVE IN
ON-DEMAND SPIN BIKING CLASSES
ACROSS THE WORLD.
>> EXERCISE BIKES HAVE BEEN
AROUND FOR DECADES BUT THIS IS
REALLY THE FIRST TIME THAT A
LIVE GYM CLASS COMES RIGHT TO
YOUR HOME.
>> IT IS NEEDED BECAUSE THE
INSTRUCTORS CAN SEE YOUR
USERNAME SO THEY CAN ALWAYS
GIVE YOU A SHOUT OUT IF IT IS
YOUR BIRTHDAY OR IF IT IS A
SPECIAL RIDE.
>> HE ADMITS IT IS NOT CHEAP.
A BIKE IS $2000 IN CLASSES COST
$39 A MONTH, SIMILAR TO A REAL
GEM.
DESPITE THE COST IT IS SO
POPULAR AND IT HAS CREATED A
COMMUNITY WHERE DAVID HAS MADE
A NEW GROUP OF FRIENDS.
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE
WHO ARE OUT THERE STRUGGLING
WITH SOMETHING.
WHETHER IT IS WEIGHT LOSS OR
WHETHER IT IS WHAT SOMEBODY
MIGHT BE BATTLING CANCER.HIS
COMMUNITY REALLY ROWS BEHIND
IT.
>> OTHER WORKOUT BUSINESSES ARE
MOVING TO THE STREAMING MODEL
TO BUT WITH SMALL STORES AND
TOP-OF-THE-LINE EQUIPMENT IS
THE LEADER WRITER AND MAKES
WORKOUT DVDS LOOK LIKE A OLD
VHS TAPE OF $2000 IS TOO STEEP
FOR YOU.
THIS INTO CHECK OF OTHER
VIRTUAL GEMS LIKE BEACH PARTY,
STREAM CLASSES WITHOUT THE
BICYCLE.
SO YOU DO NOT WASTE YOUR MONEY
♪ We buy any car ♪
♪ Any make, any model,
any age, any price ♪
♪ From 50 bucks to 100 grand ♪
♪ We buy any car ♪
♪ Any, any, any, any ♪
At webuyanycar.com,
the gimmicks stop with our ads.
Trading in our selling
your car is hassle-free
with just three easy steps.
One, get your free
online valuation.
Two, drive to your local
car buying centre.
And three,
walk out with your check
in as little as 30 minutes.
So don't wait.
Get your free online
valuation now.
♪ Find out how much
your car's worth ♪
♪ At webuyanycar.com ♪
>>Adrianna: WE WERE JUST THINK
WE ARE READY FOR SUMMER.
>>Steve: A LITTLE BIT OF GREEN
AND SOME SUNSHINE.
SUNSHINE AS WE MOVE THROUGH
WEDNESDAY BUT WERE ONLY OUT
MONDAY.
IT WINTRY MIX WILL CONTINUE TO
THE NORTH AND WEST OF TOWN.
WE HAVE WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY
FOR FREDERICK IN THE
SURROUNDING COUNTIES.
RAIN MODERATE TIMES DURING THE
AFTERNOON HOURS AND IT WILL BE
WINDY BUT MODERATE ON WEDNESDAY
THE UPPER 40S.
JON HUSTED IS LOOKING GOOD IF
YOU ARE GOING TO BE OUT AND
ABOUT AND THE TEMPERATURES WILL
BE IN THE MID-50S AND MID-50S
ON FRIDAY WITH THE BETTER
CHANCE FOR WHAT WEATHER LATER
IN THE DAY.
AS A CALL FROM MR. AND THAT IS
GOING TO DROP OUR TEMPERATURES
FOR THE UPCOMING WEEKEND.
BILL KELLY WILL BE IN AT 4:00
AND HE WILL HAVE A FRESH UPDATE
ON OUR FUTURECAST AND WHAT TO
EXPECT FOR TONIGHT.
WE ARE WAITING FOR THE WINTER
STORM WATCH OFF TO THE NORTH
AND WEST OF US TO CONVERT TO
EITHER WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY
OR WINTER STORM WARNING.
OR MAYBE IT WILL JUST
DISAPPEAR.
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>> NOW ABC7 NEWS AT NOON.
ON YOUR SIDE.
WE BEGIN WITH A BREAKING NEWS
ALERT.
>>Adrianna: THAT BREAKING NEWS
COMING FROM THE WHITE HOUSE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP DECLARING A
NATIONAL EMERGENCY FOR HIS
BORDER WALL.
EVEN THOUGH CONGRESS PASSED A
BIPARTISAN BILL TO KEEP THE
GOVERNMENT OPEN AND PROVIDE
FUNDS FOR BORDER SECURITY.
THE MOVE, EVEN THE PRESIDENT OF
NOLOGY, WILL LIKELY DRAW OUT A
LONG TIME LEGAL WAR.
SERENA MARSHALL HAS THE
DETAILS.
>> UNABLE TO GET THE FUNDS THAT
HE WANTED, PRESIDENT TRUMP
GOING AT IT ALONE.
SIGNING THE BY PERSON FUNDING
BILL BUT ALSO DECLARING A
NATIONAL EMERGENCY.
>> IT IS A GREAT THING TO DO.
BECAUSE WE HAVE INVASION OF
DRUGS, INVASION OF GANGS AND
INVASION OF PEOPLE AND IS
UNACCEPTABLE.
>> WITH THIS MOVE THE PRESENT
IS SECURING NEARLY $8 BILLION
FOR HIS BORDER WALL.
NEARLY $1.4 BILLION FROM THE
BORDER SECURITY BILL WITH THE
EMERGENCY DECLARATION ANOTHER
THREE AND HALF BILLION FROM THE
PENTAGON CONSTRUCTION BUDGET.
THE REMAINING FUNDS THROUGH
EXECUTIVE ORDERS INCLUDING $600
BILLION FROM THE TREASURY
DEPARTMENT AND AN ADDITIONAL 2
AND A HALF BILLION DOLLARS FROM
THE PENTAGON.
THE DECLARATION, NOT ENTIRELY
UNEXPECTED.
DURING THE 35 DAY SHUTDOWN, THE
PRESIDENT HAD SAID.> PEOPLE
EITHER HAVE A WIN OR I WILL
DECLARE ANATIONAL EMERGENCY.
> IT IS COMMENTS LIKE THAT
THAT HAVE DEMOCRATS CALLING THE
MOVE A LAWLESS ACT IN .
>> USING THIS TO MEET A
CAMPAIGN PROMISE IS SIMPLY A
TERRIBLE IDEA.
>> AS A CITIZEN, DONALD TRUMP
CRITICIZED PRESIDENT OBAMA FOR
TAKING EXECUTIVE ACTION FIVE
YEARS AGO FOR THE DREAMERS.
TO THINK THAT POLICE MUST NOT
LET PRESIDENT OBAMA SUBVERT THE
CONSTITUTION FOR HIS OWN USE.
BEFORE THE SPEAKER EVEN SAID
THE BILL TO THE PRESIDENT SHE
OFFERED A WARNING.
>> WE WILL NOT HAVE AN END RUN
AROUND THE CONGRESS OF THE
UNITED STATES.
>> FOLLOWING THE PRESIDENT'S
REMARKS, THEY ISSUED A JOINT
STATEMENT SAYING THE
PRESIDENT'S ACTIONS CLEARLY
VIOLATE THE CONSTITUTION AND IF
UNCHECKED WILL FUNDAMENTALLY
CHECK OF THE ALTAR BALANCE OF
POWER.
>>Adrianna: TO SEE MORE OF THE
PRESIDENT'S COMMENTS TODAY AND
TO FOLLOW ALL THE DEVELOPERS
WITH THE BORDER WALL, DOWNLOAD
THE ABC7 NEWS APP.
>>> JUSTICE RUTH BADER GINSBURG
IS BACK IN THE SUPREME COURT
FOR THE FIRST TIME SINCE CANCER
SURGERY LEISURE.
THE COURT IS THE 85-YEAR-OLD
JUSTICE IS PARTICIPATING.
SHE HAD TWO CANCERS NOTICE FROM
HER LEFT LUNG REMOVED IN
DECEMBER AND NOW SHE IS CANCER
FREE.>>> A BEAUTIFUL WEATHER
DAY TO GET OUTSIDE FOR A LUNCH.
STEVE RUDIN IS HERE FOR A CHECK
OF THE FORECAST AND HOW WARM IT
WILL GO BEFORE THE TEMPERATURES
DROP TOMORROW.
>>Steve: LOOKING AT A NICE
AFTERNOON SHAPING UP WITH A
GOOD AMOUNT OF SUNSHINE.
THIS IS OUR BRAND-NEW VIEW FROM
TOP THE WATERGATE HOTEL LOOKING
AT THE POTOMAC RIVER.
WE HAVE GEORGETOWN RIGHT OVER
HERE AND ON THE OTHER SIDE OF
THE BRIDGE IS ROSLYN.
A NICE AFTERNOON IF YOU ARE
GOING TO BE OUT AND ABOUT.
TEMPERATURE ALREADY IN THE
LOWER 60S AT REAGAN NATIONAL
AIRPORT, MID-60S IN LEESBURG,
57 DEGREES RIGHT NOW IN
WINCHESTER.
I DO WANT TO SHOW YOU STORM
WATCH 7 SATELLITE AND RADAR
WITH CLOUD COVER OFF TO THE
WEST OF US AND IT WILL
EVENTUALLY MAKE ITS WAY TO OUR
AREA LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
FORECAST FOR TODAY, IT DOES NOT
GET MUCH BETTER THAN THIS FOR
THE MIDDLE OF FEBRUARY.
WE ARE CALLING FOR A DAYTIME HI
IN THE MIDDLE 60S WITH ADDED
AFTERNOON CLOUDS WITH COMING UP
IN A FEW MINUTES I AM TRACKING
OUR NEXT WEATHER MAKER THAT
MIGHT BRING A LITTLE BIT OF
WINTRY WEATHER TO PARTS OF THE
DMV.
I WILL TELL YOU EXACTLY WHERE,
GIVE YOU THE TIMING AND LOOK
AHEAD TO PRESIDENT'S DAY IN
JUST A FEW MINUTES.
>Adrianna: VICE PRESIDENT
MIKE PENCE HEADED TO MUNICH,
GERMANY AFTER MAKING HIS FIRST
VISIT TO AUSCHWITZ.
IT WAS A CONCENTRATION CAMP
OCCUPIED IN POLAND DURING WORLD
WAR II.
HE PAID TRIBUTE AFTER HE.
>> THERE IS A DEEPLY DISTURBING
TREND.
ANOTHER CHILD IS THE VICTIM OF
GUN VIOLENCE.
THIS TIME IT IS A 12-YEAR-OLD
BOY HIT BY A STRAY BULLET IN A
SHOOTOUT ON POND STREET IN
NORTHEAST.
POLICE CHIEF PETER NEWSOM
CALLING FOR A STOP TO THE
SENSELESS VIOLENCE.EANWHILE
THE SEARCH IS ON FOR THE
SHOOTER AND JOHN RESULTS IS
FOLLOWING THE INVESTIGATION FOR
US.
>>John: THAT IS RIGHT.
THIS BOY IS FIGHTING FOR HIS
LIFE AT THIS HOUR AND NOT A
GOOD TREND.
THE THIRD CHILD TO BE STRUCK BY
A STRAY BULLET IN D.C. SO FAR
THIS YEAR.
WHEN D.C. POLICE AND PARENTS
ARRIVED HERE IN NORTHEAST
YESTERDAY, THEY FOUND THE
12-YEAR-OLD BOY AND RESPONSIVE
OUTSIDE HERE NEAR HIS HOME.
OU CAN SEE AT THIS HOUR,
POLICE STILL HAVE POND STREET
CLOSED OFF.
THIS IS CLOSE TO THE KENILWORTH
RECREATION CENTER AND POOL WITH
THE POLICE CHIEF MAKING IT VERY
CLEAR THAT THIS WAS NOT A
SINGLE GUN INCIDENT.
THERE WERE MULTIPLE PUPPIES OUT
HERE LAST NIGHT.
HE IS NOT SURE IF THERE WAS AN
EXCHANGE OF GUNFIRE BUT BULLETS
DEFINITELY CAME FROM DIFFERENT
GUNS AND OUR VIDEO INDICATES
THAT OUR CAMERA CAPTURING 48
EVIDENCE MARKERS AND MOST OF
THOSE WERE SHELL CASINGS.T
LEAST ONE CAR WINDOW WAS BLOWN
OUT.
THE POINT WAS RUSHED TO THE
HOSPITAL IN CRITICAL CONDITION
AT THIS HOUR.
>> WE HAD A LITTLE KID, LITTLE
BABY OVER AT THE BUS STOP AND
WE HAD A SIX-YEAR-OLD THE OTHER
NIGHT WHO WAS IN THE BACKSEAT
OF A CAR THE 2400 BLOCK OF
ALABAMA AND NOW WE HAVE A
12-YEAR-OLD KID WHO SHOULD BE
OUT OR AT HOME ENJOYING HIS
EVENING.
HE IS AT ONE OF OUR LOCAL
HOSPITAL STRUGGLING BECAUSE HE
HAS BEEN SHOT.
IT HAS GOT TO STOP.>John:
NEIGHBOR STILL ABC7 NEWS THAT
THEY ALSO HEARD GUNSHOTS AROUND
THE SAME TIME THE NIGHT BEFORE.
WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
AUTHORITIES ARE ASKING FOR THE
PUBLIC TO BE ON THE LOOKOUT FOR
A SILVER VEHICLE WITH AT LEAST
FOUR PEOPLE INSIDE.
POLICE SAY ONE PERSON WEARING
AN ORANGE TREE HERE LAST NIGHT.
IN NORTHEAST WASHINGTON JOHN
RESULTS ABC7 NEWS.
>>Adrianna: THE FIRST OF FOUR
DAMASCUS HIGH SCHOOL JUNIOR
VARSITY PLAYERS ACCUSED OF
RAPING TEAMMATES WITH A
BROOMSTICK, FACING A JUDGE
TODAY.
THE 15 OR ASKING FOR HIS CASE
TO BE TRIED IN JUVENILE COURT.
HIS THREE CODEFENDANTS WILL
HAVE SIMILAR HEARINGS IN THE
COMING WEEKS.
>>> THIS WEEK WE REPORTED ON A
FIGHT INSIDE THE HIGH SCHOOL
AND A STUDENT IS STILL IN THE
HOSPITAL WITH A FRACTURED
SCHOOL AND A BLOOD CLOT WITH
ABC SEVEN LEARNING PROTOCOLS
FROM THE SCHOOL TO REPORT TO
NOT WHEN ONE WERE NOT FOLLOWED
IN THIS CASE BUT IT WAS THE
STUDENTS FATHER WHO CALLED
9-1-1. WE HAVE ASKED FOR
INTERVIEWS WITH THE
SUPERINTENDENT AS WELL AS
McGRUDER'S PRINCIPAL AND BOTH
HAVE SAID THAT THEY ARE
UNAVAILABLE.
>>> COMING UP NEXT AT NOON.
KIDS ARE SUPPOSED BE ON THEIR
BEST BEHAVIOR AND STRENGTH THAT
ALSO APPLY TO PARENTS?
ONE WOULD THINK.
LOOKING BACK MORE ON THIS
WRESTLING MATCH MELEE THAT
HAPPENED OFF THE MATCH AND SEND
THESE PARENTS TO TIMEOUT.
PLUS GETTING A GIFT WRONG, IT
SOMETIMES HAPPENS.
BUT WHEN SOMEONE TELLS YOU WHAT
THEY WANT IS TO GET IT WRONG,
BACK TO BE A BIG PROBLEM.
MISTAKE THAT TURNED A WOMAN'S
VALENTINE'S DAY VERY SOUR.
>>Eric: ON THE ROADWAYS HIS
FRIDAY AFTERNOON WE HAVE A FEW
SLOW SPOTS TO WORRY ABOUT
STARTING OFF ON 66 NEAR FAIRFAX
COUNTY PARKWAY, BOTH DIRECTIONS
SEEM TO BE OPEN FROM EARLIER
WORK ZONES AT THIS POINT.
LITTLE BIT OF VOLUME TO CONTEND
WITH AT THIS TIME.
FOR THE MOST PART TRAFFIC IS
MOVING.
CAPITAL BELTWAY INNER LOOP
HEADING OUT OF SPRINGFIELD AND
LOOKS LIKE ANOTHER MOBILE
BROOKSTONE HERE.
A BIT OF A SUDDEN JAM HEADING
UP THIS WAY OUT OF SPRINGFIELD.
SOUTHBOUND 95 WILL BEGIN TO
SLOW DOWN ALREADY FROM MORNING
OVER THE UPPER POND OVER THE
BRIDGE.
THEY HAVE A WORK ZONE PAST ROOT
FOR INTO FT. SILL BLOCKING THE
LEFT LANE INTO ALLENTOWN ROAD.
IT DOES SLOW THINGS DOWN BACK
TO
>>Adrianna: THIS WAS CAUGHT ON
CAMERA AND YOU SEE HERE PARENTS
FIGHTING DURING THEIR
CHILDREN'S WRESTLING MATCH.
THIS HAPPENED IN WISCONSIN.
THINGS GOT UGLY FAST.
YOU CAN SEE A WOMAN DRESSED IN
A BLACK SHIRT IN A HEATED
EXCHANGE WITH ANOTHER MOM.
THEN A MAN GETS UP INTO HER
FACE AND HOW TO GET PULLED AWAY
BY SEVERAL OTHER PARENTS.
THEN THE TWO WOMEN SCUFFLING
THEY FALL TO THE GROUND ALL
BALL THE KIDS ARE STILL
COMPETING ON THE MAP.
ALL OF THESE PARENTS WERE ALL
THREE INVOLVED WERE CITED FOR
DISORDERLY CONDUCT.>> FOR
THE FIRST TIME SINCE BEING
RELEASED FROM AN IMMIGRATION
RETENTION CENTER, ROBERT 21
SAVAGE ADDRESSING HIS ARREST ON
CAMERA.
THE 26-YEAR-OLD BORN IN ENGLAND
CAME TO THE U.S. AT SEVEN YEARS
OLD.
HE WAS RAISED IN ATLANTA BUT IS
LIVING HERE ON AN EXPIRED VISA.
HERE IS WHAT HE HAD TO SAY TO
ABC'S LINDSAY DAVIS.
>> AT A CERTAIN POINT, 2006
YOUR VISA EXPIRED.
>> I DO NOT KNOW WHAT HE VISA
WAS.
I WAS SEVEN WHEN I FIRST CAME
HERE.
AND YOU I WAS NOT BORN HERE,
BUT I DO NOT KNOW WHAT, WHAT
THAT MEANT AS FAR AS WHEN I
TRANSITIONED INTO AN ADULT HOW
IT WOULD AFFECT MY LIFE.
I WAS NOT HIDING IT, BUT IT WAS
LIKE I DO NOT WANT TO GET
DEPORTED SO NOT COME OUT AND
SAY, I WAS NOT BORN HERE.
I HAVE BEEN HERE 20 YEARS, 19
YEARS.
THIS IS ALL I KNOW.OU KNOW
WHAT I AM SAYING?
I DO NOT FEEL LIKE YOU SHOULD
BE ARRESTED AND PUT IN A PLACE
WHERE A MURDER WOULD BE FOR
JUST BEING IN THE COUNTRY.
FOR TOO LONG.
>> THE ROBBERS REPRESENTATIVES
SAY THEY ARE IN THE PROCESS OF
SECURING HIS IMMIGRATION STATUS
TO MAKE HIM A CITIZEN.
GOING FORWARD, HE SAYS HE WILL
DEVOTE TIME TO BRING AWARENESS
TO IMMIGRATION ISSUES.>>
POLICE IN CHICAGO SAY TWO MEN
QUESTION IN THE PORTAGE ATTACK
ON JUSSIE SMOLLETT ARE INDEED
SUSPECTS.
ONE OF THE MEN HAS A CONNECTION
TO THE SHOW.
>> AUTHORITIES IN CHICAGO
BELIEVE THEY FOUND TWO
POTENTIAL SUSPECTS SEEN HERE ON
THE SURVEILLANCE IMAGE FROM THE
NIGHT OF THE ALLEGED ATTACK ON
JUSSIE SMOLLETT.> HAVE YOU
SEEN THAT IMAGE AND DID YOU
BELIEVE THAT THEY COULD
POSSIBLY BE THE ATTACKERS,
>> I DO NOT HAVE ANY DOUBT IN
MY MIND.
THAT IS THAT IS THEM.
NEVER DID.
>> THE TREATMENT WERE PICKED UP
FOR QUESTIONING AT THE AIRPORT
ON WEDNESDAY.
AS THE NETWORK TURNED ON A
FLIGHT FROM NIGERIA.
WHAT AN ACTOR WHO HAS APPEARED
ON JUSSIE SMOLLETT SHOW,
EMPIRE.
POLICE RAIDED THEIR HOMES,
TAKING SHOES, ELECTRONIC
DEVICES AND OTHER ITEMS POLICE
BELIEVE COULD BE KEY TO THE
INVESTIGATION.
THIS POINT, PLEASE DO ABC NEWS
THAT THEY ARE INVESTIGATING
WHETHER THE TWO INDIVIDUALS
COMMITTED THE ATTACK OR WHETHER
THE ATTACK HAPPENED AT ALL.
INVESTIGATORS SPENT PART OF
THURSDAY IS GETTING JUSSIE
SMOLLETT ABOUT THE INCIDENT.
THE ACTOR INSISTS HE IS TELLING
THE TRUTH.
>> WHO WOULD MAKE SOMETHING
LIKE THIS UP OR ADD SOMETHING
TO IT OR WHATEVER, IT MAYBE. I
CANNOT EVEN, I AM AN ADVOCATE,
I RESPECT TOO MUCH, THE PEOPLE
WHO I AM NOW ONE OF THOSE
PEOPLE, WHO HAS BEEN ATTACKED
IN ANY WAY.
YOU DO SUCH A DISSERVICE WHEN
YOU A LOT ABOUT THINGS LIKE
THIS.
>> IN A STATEMENT, 21ST CENTURY
FOLKS SAY THEY CONTINUE TO
STAND BEHIND JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
SO FAR, NO CHARGES HAVE BEEN
FILED AGAINST THE TWO POTENTIAL
SUSPECTS.AGGIE RULLI ABC
NEWS NEAR.
>>Adrianna: A COUPLE IN
KENTUCKY IS LAUGHING TODAY
ABOUT A VALENTINE'S DAY MIXER.
ALAN HARRIS ASKED HIS WIFE NINA
WHAT SHE WANTED FOR VALENTINE'S
DAY AND SHE SAID SHE WANTED
TULIPS.
HE MISSED UNDERSTOOD AND HE
HEARD TURNIPS.
SO HE WENT OUT AND GOT HER SOME
TURNIPS AND HE MADE THEM AS
ROMANTIC AS POSSIBLE.
>> I WENT AND GOT THE BOOK AND
PUT THE TURNIPS IN THE BUCKET
THAT SAID I LOVE YOU ON IT I
GOT HER COFFEE AND HE COULD GO.
>> WHEN I GOT UP AND HAD MY
FIRST CUP OF COFFEE, HE SAID
OH, A TURNIPS ARE HERE.
AND I SAID TURNIPS?
>>Adrianna: WHEN ALAN REALIZED
HE MADE A MISTAKE, HE QUICKLY
WENT TO THE STORE AND BOUGHT
HER SOME TULIPS AND A BALLOON.
SHE DOES APPRECIATE HIS EFFORT
AND SAID THIS FANTASY HAS BEEN
SPECIAL IN MANY WAYS.
>>Steve: THAT IS REALLY NICE.
>>Adrianna: IT IS NOT A BAD
STORY BUT HE THOUGHT HE HEARD
SOMETHING AND HE GOT HER A
VALENTINE'S DAY GIFT, HE JUST
MISUNDERSTOOD.
>>Steve: WHAT DO YOU EVEN DO
TURNIPS?
DO YOU MAKE A SOUP OR DO YOU
ROAST THEM?
>>Adrianna: I DO NOT KNOW.
>>Steve: GIVE THEM AS
VALENTINE'S DAY GIFTS INSTEAD
OF TULIPS.
IN A STORY WITH A NICE ENDING.
>> TODAY, WOW.
WHAT AN ABSOLUTE GORGEOUS
AFTERNOON.HIS IS OUR
BRAND-NEW CAMERA ATOP THE
WATERGATE HOTEL IN NORTHWEST
D.C.. NOW WE HAVE IT TURNED
TOWARDS GEORGETOWN UNIVERSITY.
THIS CAMERA CAN SEE EVERYTHING
FROM THE RIVER TO ROSSLYN OVER
TOWARD THE KENNEDY CENTER AND
THE AIR FORCE MEMORIAL DURING
THE NEXT HOUR I WILL GIVE YOU A
TOUR OF ALL THE GREAT SHOTS
THAT WE HAVE.
HEREIS OUR VANTAGE POINT OVER
NATIONAL HARBOR WITH A FEW
CLOUDS OUT THERE RIGHT NOW.
OTHERWISE IT IS QUITE, IT IS
DRY AND IS VERY MILD .
OVERLOOKING THE TIDAL BAIN,
NICE AFTERNOON AND I HOPE YOU
HAVE THE CHANCE TO GET OUT
THERE AND ENJOY IT.LOOK AT
THESE TEMPERATURES.
MY GOODNESS PAID FOR THE MIDDLE
OF FEBRUARY WE ARE IN THE
MIDDLE 60S OVER AT LEESBURG.
63 IN GAITHERSBURG, SAME IN
FREDERICK AND NOW 61 AT
ANDREWS, ANNAPOLIS AT 64.
THIS A LITTLE COOLER OFF TOWARD
THE NORTH AND WEST OF US.
CUMBERLAND, MARYLAND REPORTING
IN A CHILLY 42 DEGREES.
CHECK OF THE WINDS AND IS A
LITTLE BIT BREEZY UP THERE WITH
15 TO 20 MILE-PER-HOUR WINDS.
THE TEMPERATURE CHANGE.
ESTERDAY AT THIS TIME, AROUND
15 TO 22 DEGREES WARMER.
IT WILL NOT LAST LONG.
WE HAVE A COLD FRONT ON THE WAY
LATER THIS AFTERNOON INTO THE
EVENING HOURS BUT THAT WILL
CHANGE OUR AIR MASS FOR THE
UPCOMING WEEKEND.
IN THE MEANTIME, WE ARE BASKING
IN A GOOD AMOUNT OF SUNSHINE OR
BRIGHT SKIES, SHOULD SAY WITH
ADDED CAUSE UP TO THE WEST OF
US.
YOU MIGHT SEE A STRAY SPRINKLE
OR TWO BUT IT WILL NOT AMOUNT
TO WHOLE LOT.
YOU WILL GOING TO BE OUT AND
ABOUT WJLA 24/7 TIME HOUR,
TEMPERATURES IN THE 60S WITH A
LIGHT JACKET IS ALL YOU WILL
NEED.
LATER ON THIS EVENING THE
TEMPERATURES BEGIN TO SLIDE,
MAYBE CHECKING OUT A MOVIE OR
WALKING ON 14TH STREET OR
GEORGETOWN OR WHEREVER YOU
MAYBE GOING.
WE ARE LOOKING AT ADDED CLOUD
COVER.
FOR TONIGHT, IT WILL BE COLD UP
THERE 20 TO 38 DEGREES AND THAT
IS TEMPERATURES BUT UNDER
MOSTLY CLOUDY SKIES.
IT WILL BE A CHILLY START YOUR
DAY TOMORROW.
ALSO, SOME OF YOU MIGHT BE
LOOKING AT A LITTLE BIT OF A
WINTRY MIX.
HOUR BY HOUR FOR TOMORROW AND
WE WILL CALL FOR MOSTLY CLOUDY
SKIES WITH A CHANCE FOR A
LITTLE BIT OF SLEEP MIXING IN
WITH RAIN AND SNOW AND AS WE
HEAD TO THE FIRST PART OF THE
DAY, BUT THEN WE SHOULD SEE A
GOOD AMOUNT OF CLEARING DURING
THE AFTERNOON HOURS.
TEMPERATURES THAT WILL MAKE IT
INTO THE 40S BUT HERE IS OUR
FUTURECAST 90 WANT TO START WE
ARE RIGHT NOW.
IT IS DRY UP THERE, OBVIOUSLY.
AS YOU MOVE THROUGH THE EVENING
HOURS WE DO STAY MAINLY DRY.
THEN, LATER ON TONIGHT IN EARLY
TOMORROW MORNING WE HAVE A
SYSTEM THAT IS GOING TO MOVE
JUST TO THE SOUTH OF THE D.C.
METRO AREA.
BRICK YOU SEE THE AREA SHADED
IN BLUE, IT MAY SEE A SLUSHY
ACCUMULATION ON GRASSY AREAS.
THIS INCLUDES THE DISTRICT AND
ARLINGTON AND ALEXANDRIA BUT
FOR AS QUICKLY AS IT ARRIVES,
THAT IS HOW FAST IT IS OUT OF
FEAR.
BY NOONTIME TOMORROW OUR SKIES
BEGIN TO CLEAR AND GARRETT,
ALLEGHENY AND WASHINGTON
COUNTIES AND QUESTION MARYLAND
WITH A LOT OF SUNSHINE.
LATER TOMORROW AFTERNOONAT 5:00
WE WILL DEAL WITH A NICE SUNSET
AROUND THE DMV AS THE COOLER
AIR OVEREXPOSE THE REGION.
HOW MUCH THE ARE WE TALKING
ABOUT?
LESS THAN AN INCH , IF EVEN
THAT.
ONCE AGAIN SOUTH OF THE D.C.
METRO AREA AND WE ARE TALKING
ABOUT OVER TOWARD
FREDERICKSBURG AND CULPEPER.
ONCE AGAIN, MAINLY ON GRASSY
AREAS AND WE ARE NOT GOING TO
SEE A WHOLE LOT OTHER THAN A
NUISANCE IN TERMS OF THE
WEATHER.
HERE IS OUR FORECAST.
THIS IS A LITTLE BIT OF
ADJUSTING HERE.
WE ARE LOOKING TEMPERATURES IN
THE 40S TOMORROW AND WE STAY IN
THE 40S AND NEXT WEEK.
EVEN THE 30S BEFORE WE FINALLY
START TO WARM THINGS UP JUST A
LITTLE BIT.
ONCE AGAIN, TOMORROW YOU ARE
DRIVING DO NOT EXPECT TO SEE A
BIG PROBLEM.
HOWEVER, WHAT ROADWAYS AROUND
HERE TO SLOW THINGS DOWN BUT
THANKFULLY THE TIME IS WORKING
TO OUR ADVANTAGE.
IT IS A WEEKEND MORNING, EARLY
ON AND TOMORROW NIGHT LOOKING
GOOD.
>>Adrianna: THANK YOU STEVE.
COMING UP ON ABC7 NEWS AT NOON.
You might take something
for your heart...
or joints.
But do you take something
for your brain.
With an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish,
Prevagen has been shown
in clinical trials
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>Adrianna: HAPPENING TONIGHT
20/20 WITH A NEW INSIDE OF THE
HORRIFYING KILLING SPREE OF TED
BUNDY 30 YEARS AFTER HIS
EXECUTION.
HE ADMITTED TO MURDERING AT
LEAST 30 WOMEN AND MANY OF THEM
HE KIDNAPPED AND SEXUALLY
ASSAULTED.DESPITE HIS
CONFESSION, AUTHORITIES DO
BELIEVE THERE MIGHT HAVE BEEN
MANY MORE VICTIMS.
ABC DEBORAH ROBERTS JOINS US
LIVE WITH A PREVIEW OF WHAT WE
WILL SEE TONIGHT.
IT IS ALWAYS GREAT TO HAVE YOU.
I WANT TO START BY ASKING YOU,
WHY ARE AMERICANS AND PEOPLE IN
GENERAL SO FASCINATED WITH TED
BUNDY?
>> THAT IS A VERY GOOD QUESTION
ANDWE WONDERED THE SAME THING.
MANY THINK ABOUT IT, SADLY, HE
HAD ALL THE ELEMENTS OF
FASCINATION.
HE WAS CHARMING, GOOD-LOOKING.
REMEMBER, HE EVEN REPRESENT
HIMSELF AS HIS OWN LAWYER IN
HIS TRIAL.
THIS WAS A GUY WHO, NOT ONLY ,
TRICKED A LOT OF WOMEN AND LED
THEM TO THEIR DEATH BUT WAS
ABLE TO CHARM HIS JAILERS,
CHARM, BASICALLY COURTHOUSE
WORKERS IN AUTHORITIES.
NOBODY THOUGHT THIS WAS THE
KIND OF GUY WHO WAS THE PICTURE
IN FACE OF HORRIBLE CRIME AND
LET ALONE, A SERIAL KILLER.
I THINK BECAUSE HE WAS SUCH A
SMOOTH OPERATOR AND EVEN TO THE
VERY END, INVESTIGATORS WANTED
TO TALK WITH THEM.
HE BEGAN TO TALK ABOUT HIS
CRIMES AT THE VERY END BEFORE
HE WAS EXECUTED.
PEOPLE WANTED TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT WENT ON INSIDE HIS MIND.
A MAN HE WAS SEEMINGLY SO
NORMAL, HAD STUDIED PSYCHOLOGY
IN COLLEGE, HAD A LAW STUDENT,
HAD A GIRLFRIEND.
CUT THE PICTURE OF THE GUY NEXT
DOOR BUT HAD THE DARK SIDE AND
PRAYED ON WOMEN IN SUCH A
VICIOUS, VICIOUS AWFUL WAYS.
>>Adrianna: WE KNOW TOWARD THE
END OF HIS LIFE BEFORE HE WAS
EXECUTED, HE DID SIT DOWN AND
TALK WITH INVESTIGATORS.
THEY HAVE SAID THAT HE GAVE
THEM QUITE A BIT O INSIGHT ON
HOW SERIAL KILLERS WORK.
>> HE DID.
WHAT WAS INTERESTING WAS THAT
HE WAS STILL WHEELING AND
DEALING ALL THE WAY TO THE END.
HE WOULD WITHHOLD THE
INFORMATION AND HE KNEW THAT HE
COULD USE IT TO BUY A LITTLE
TIME, EVEN BEFORE HIS
EXECUTION.
THIS WAS A GUY WHO NEVER
STOPPED MANIPULATING, BUT HE
DID EVENTUALLY, AS YOU SAID,
START TO COME CLEAN ABOUT SOME
OF THE CRIMES THAT HE
COMMITTED.
TO SPELL A LITTLE BIT MORE TO
INVESTIGATORS.
TONIGHT ON A ONE, BESIDES JUST
THESE HORRIBLE CRIMES YOU WILL
HEAR FROM THE VICTIM'S
THEMSELVES.
SOME OF THEM THAT ESCAPED HIS
CLUTCHES IN FLORIDA THAT WERE
TRACKED BY HIM BUT MANAGED TO
GET AWAY.
YOU WILL HEAR FROM
INVESTIGATORS ABOUT WHAT THEY
LEARNED FROM HIM AND HOW THEY
WERE ABLE TO TRACK HIM DOWN.
ONE OF THE MOST NOTORIOUS
MODERN-DAY SERIAL KILLERS AND
ONE THAT PEOPLE STILL SEEM TO
BE TALKING ABOUT ALL THESE
DECADES LATER.
>>Adrianna: WOW.
THAT 20/20 IS A TWO HOUR EVENT
STARTING AT 9:00 TONIGHT.
GREAT TO HAVE YOU.
>>Adrianna: HOLLYWOOD ON THE
POTOMAC IS ALIVE AND WELL TODA
.
IF YOU ARE HEADED TO THE
NATIONAL MALL YOU COULD SEE
CAMERAS AND COSTUMES.
THE HULU HIT SHOW, THE
HANDMAID'S TALE IS FILMING.
WE ARE TOLD THEY WILL BE
SHOOTING UNTIL THE END OF THE
DAY.
>>> AT LEAST THEY HAD A NICE
DAY TO SHOOT.
>>Steve: ,VISIT D.C. AND YOU
NEVER KNOW WHAT YOU WILL SEE,
MAYBE A MOVIE CAKE.
>>> TODAY IS THE DAY TO GET
OUTSIDE AND GRAB A BITE TO EAT
OR MAYBE GOOD TO HEAR ROOF DECK
IF YOU HAVE ONE.
OR JUST THE FRONT PORCH SOUNDS
GOOD TO ME.
64, 65 DEGREES FOR THIS
AFTERNOON AND MUCH COLDER
TOMORROW WITH A WINTRY MIX.
MAINLY DURING THE MORNING HOURS
SOUTH OF D.C.. YOU MIGHT SEE
>> YOU ARE WATCHING ABC7 NEWS
AT NOON.
ON YOUR SIDE.
>>Adrianna: PRESIDENT TRUMP
SIGNING A FUNNY BILL TO PREVENT
ANOTHER PARTIAL GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN.
AND ALSO DECLARING A NATIONAL
EMERGENCY ON THE SOUTHERN
BORDER.
HIS ILLUSTRATION BELIEVES THAT
OCCLUSION ALLOWS YOU TO
REALLOCATE BILLIONS OF DOLLARS
FOR HIS BORDER WALL.
THE PRESIDENT DEFENDED HIS
DECISION DURING A NEWS
CONFERENCE IN THE ROSE GARDEN A
FEW MOMENTS AGO.
>> AND WE WILL HAVE A NATIONAL
EMERGENCY AND DID WE WILL BE
SUED AND THEY WILL SUE US IN
THE NINTH CIRCUIT.
EVEN THOUGH IT SHOULD NOT BE
THERE.
WE WILL POSSIBLY GET A BAD
RULING AND THEN WE WILL GET
ANOTHER BAD RULING AND THEN THE
PEOPLE END UP IN THE SUPREME
COURT AND THEN HOPEFULLY WE
WILL GET A FAIR SHAKE.
THEN WE WILL WIN AT THE SUPREME
COURT.
>>Adrianna: CONGRESS NOW HAS 15
DAYS TO PASS A RESOLUTION
DISAPPROVING OF THE
ECLARATION.G OF THE
A NUMBER OF REPUBLICANS ARE
LIKELY TO SUPPORT THE
RESOLUTION, SAYING THE
DECLARATION SETS A DANGEROUS
PRECEDENT.
>>> OF COURSE TO SEE MORE OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S COMMENTS
TODAY INTERVAL ALL DEVELOPMENTS
WITH THIS BOARDWALK, DOWNLOAD
THE ABC7 NEWS APP.
>>> AMAZON DELIVERED IN CRYSTAL
CITY BUT THE GIANT IS PULLING
OUT OF ITS NEW YORK CITY HQ2
SPOTTED SIDING MAJOR POLITICAL
OPPOSITION OVER THAT NEARLY $3
BILLION OF INCENTIVES PROMISED
TO THE COMPANY.
AMAZON IS STILL COMMITTED TO
VIRGINIA AND THE COMPANY CLAIMS
IT IS NOT LOOKING FOR A NEW
PLACE, BUT MARYLAND GOVERNOR,
LARRY HOGAN SAYS HIS
MINISTRATIONHAS HAD PULMONARY
DISCUSSIONS ABOUT EXPANSION IN
HIS DAY.
>>> A TRAFFIC ALERT FOR YOU.
CHRIS WILL BE INSTALLING THE .
DEMONSTRATE COURSE AT HOME TO
HIS BOSTON NEIGHBORHOOD AND
DISCLOSURES BEGIN AT 2:00 THIS
AFTERNOON AND THEY WENT 6:00
SUNDAY NIGHT.
FOR MUCH OF THE TIME WILSON
BOULEVARD WILL BE CLOSED
BETWEEN NORTH OAKLAND AND NORTH
TAYLOR STREETS.
SECTIONS OF POLISH, QUINCY,
RANDOLPH AND STEWART STREET
NEAR WILSON BOULEVARD WILL ALSO
BE CLOSED.
MOTORS ARE URGED TO USE NORTH
LEE ROAD AND FAIRFAX DRIVE TO
BYPASS THE CONSTRUCTION AREA.
>>> AND OTHER LOOK FOR ALL YOU
VIRGINIA DRIVERS WHO CAN SOON
HAVE TO WATCH OUT FOR SPEED
CAMERAS WITH A BILL TO ALLOW
THOSE CAMERAS AND VERY SPECIFIC
LOCATIONS IS AWAITING THE
GOVERNOR'S INTERPRET THOSE
PLACEMENTS AND OPERATION OF THE
SPEED CAMERAS COME WITH ALL
KINDS OF CONDITIONS.
>> VIRGINIA DRIVERS HAVE NEVER
HAD TO DEAL WITH SPEED CAMERAS,
AT LEAST NOT IN VIRGINIA.
WE HAVE THEM IN D.C. AND
MARYLAND BUT NOW IT APPEARS
THEY ARE CLOSER THAN EVER.
THEY WILL NOT JUST BE ANYWHERE
BUT IF GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM
SIGNS THE BILL THEY WOULD BE IN
pCONSTRUCTION BOXES LIKE THIS
ONE LEADING UP TO THE MEMORIAL
BRIDGE.
THE RECENT, FATAL ACCIDENTS
HAVE BEEN MORE PREVALENT THAN
EVER BEFORE IN CONSTRUCTION AND
WORK ZONES AND OTHER PEOPLE TO
BRING AND MAKE IT A SAFER
ENVIRONMENT FOR THOSE WORKING
ON OUR ROADS.
HOW WOULD IT WORK?
A POLICE OFFICER WOULD HAVE TO
BE OUT IN A ZONE WITH THEIR
LIGHTS FLASHING.
THEY WOULD HOLD A RADAR GUN OR
SPEED CAMERA GUN IN THEIR HAND
IF YOU ARE GOING MORE THAN 12
MILES PER HOUR OVER THE SPEED
LIMIT, HE WOULD THEN RECEIVE A
$125 FINE IN THE MAIL.
THERE WILL BE WARNING SIGNS
OUT, AT LEAST 1000 FEET BEFORE
THE CONSTRUCTION ZONE TO WARN
THOSE.
AT LEAST THE DRIVERS WHO ARE
PAYING ATTENTION.
AS FOR WHERE THE MONEY WILL GO.
THE $125 FINES WILL ALL GO TO
THE STATE POLICE BUDGET.
STILL NO WORD ON WHEN THE SPEED
CAMERAS COULD HIT THE ROADS IN
VIRGINIA.
REPORTING IN ARLINGTON, I AM
SAM SWEENEY ABC7 NEWS.
>>Adrianna: A LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE
RIGHT NOW AT THE CAPITAL AND
STEVE, IT IS PRETTY WINDY OUT
THERE.
BUT IT IS WARM AND ALSO THE SUN
IS PEEKING THROUGH THE CLOUDS
PARTICIPATE LOOKING AT A NICE
AFTERNOON THROUGHOUT THE DMV.
UR NEW LIFE, FROM THE
WATERGATE HOTEL LOOKING AT THE
POTOMAC, KENNEDY CENTER, THE
PENTAGON AND RIGHT OVER HERE.
LOTS OF SUNSHINE NO MATTER
WHERE YOU ARE THIS AFTERNOON.
LOOK AT THESE TEMPERATURES.
LREADY IN THE LOWER 60S AND
EVEN MIDDLE 60S TO THE WEST OF
D.C.. NOW THE 24 HOUR
TEMPERATURE CHANGE COMPARED TO
YESTERDAY AT THIS TIME, ABOUT
18 DEGREES MODERATE.
WE HAVE A COLD FRONT ON THE WAY
AND LOOK AT THE TEMPERATURE
SHIFT OFF TO THE WEST OF US.
33 DEGREES COLDER THAN JUST 24
HOURS AGO OVER IN CHICAGO.
THE COLD FRONT WILL EVENTUALLY
OVERSPREAD COLD AIR FOR THE
METRO AREA.N THE MEANTIME WE
DO HAVE WINTER WEATHER
ADVISORIES AS WE HEAD OVER TO
KENTUCKY AND SOUTHERN INDIANA
AND INTO ILLINOIS BUT IF YOU
HAVE TRAVEL PLANS TO THE ST.
LOUIS AREA, YOU MIGHT FIND THE
LATEST.
WAS FOR US YOU ARE LOOKING AT A
GOOD LOOKING AFTERNOON WITH A
COLD FRONT ON THE WAY.
EARLY FORECAST FOR YOUR
TEMPERATURES, WE ARE IN THE 60S
WITH ADDED CLOUD COVER FOR THE
AFTERNOON INTO THE EVENING
HOURS.
WE ARE TRACKING THE NEXT
WEATHER MAKER THAT PROMISES TO
BRING A LITTLE BIT OF
ACCUMULATION TO PARTS OF THE
AREA BY EARLY TOMORROW MORNING.
I WILL GIVE YOU THE TIMING WITH
A FRESHLY UPDATED FUTURECAST IN
JUST A FEW MINUTES.
>>Adrianna: IN DEVELOPMENTS NOW
WITH A STORY WE FIRST BROKE ON
SEVEN.
[SCREAMING]
>>Adrianna: THIS IS VIDEO
SHOWING A SCHOOL FIDELITY
STUDENT HERE IN INTENSIVE CARE
WITH A FRACTURED SKULL AND A
BLOOD CLOT.
ABC7 NEWS HAS NOT LEARNED THAT
SCHOOL OFFICIALS DID NOT CALL
9-1-1 BUT THE BOYS PARENTS DID
HOURS LATER.
AS MONTGOMERY COUNTY REPORTER
KEVIN LEWIS FOUND, THAT APPEARS
TO GO AGAINST THE SCHOOL'S OWN
POLICIES.
>> THIS BINDING CONTRACT SIGNED
BY AN CPS AND LOCAL LAW
ENFORCEMENT LEADERS HAS A
SECTION CALLED, INFORMATION
SHARING AND INVESTIGATIONS.T
IS LIST A HANDFUL OF CRITICAL
INCIDENTS, INCLUDING THIS, A
PHYSICAL ATTACK ON ANOTHER THAT
REQUIRES MEDICAL ATTENTION
OUTSIDEOF THE SCHOOL HEALTH
ROOM.
THE DOCUMENT EXPLAINS THE
SCHOOL MUST REPORT ALL CRITICAL
INCIDENTS, QUOTE , AS AS SOON
AS POSSIBLE.
AND BY DIRECT INDICATION WITH
THE SRO OR TO THE PUBLIC SAFETY
COMMUNICATIONS CENTER.
9-1-1. BUT MONTGOMERY COUNTY
POLICE TOLD US THAT NEVER
HAPPENED TUESDAY AFTER THIS
FIGHT AT McGRUDER HIGH SCHOOL
IN DURWOOD WHICH LEFT SHANE VAN
DYCK'S SON IN THE ICU WITH A
FRACTURED SCHOOL AND A BLOOD
CLOT.
>> THEY TOLD HIS MOTHER THAT
YOUR SON IS PEEKING AND WE
THINK YOU NEED TO TAKE HIM TO
THE EMERGENCY ROOM.
>> HE WAS LEFT TO CALL POLICE
AT 2:14 PM.
ABC7 NEWS HAS OBTAINED THE
DISPATCH ALREADY.
>> THE VICTIM WAS ASSAULTED
AROUND THAT TIME AND IS
CURRENTLY IN THE HOSPITAL.
AT CHILDREN'S.
THE FATHER IS ON SCENE.> WE
ASKED AN CPS FOR ON CAMERA
INTERVIEWS WITH SUPERINTENDENT
JACK SMITH AND OR McGRUDER
PRINCIPAL LEROY EVANS PUT BOTH
SAID THEY WERE NOT AVAILABLE.
I AM KEVIN LEWIS, ABC7 NEWS.
>>Adrianna: DURING AMERICAN
HEART MONTH, 7 ON YOUR SIDE IS
SHARING STORIES OF IMPACTS OF
HEART DISEASE.
AMY INTRODUCES US TO AN
ENDURANCE ATHLETE THAT WAS
FOCUSED ON FITNESS AND LEARN
THE WARNING SIGNS OF A DEADLY
HEART ATTACK.
>> MITCH WORKS OUT EVERY DAY.
>> I DO NOT KNOW IF THERE IS
ANYTHING MORE IMPORTANT THAN
TAKING CARE OF YOURSELF.
>> HE WOULD KNOW.
>> ON A SCALE OF 1 TO 10.8.
>> THE SENIOR VICE PRESIDENT OF
FITNESS FOR WHEN MY FITNESS
STARTED MAKING HIS HELD A TOP
PRIORITY AT AGE 15.
>> I DO NOT THINK THERE IS
ANYTHING MORE IMPORTANT.
>> A LITTLE MORE THAN A YEAR
AGO, THE UNTHINKABLE HAPPENED.
>> THEY GAVE ME THE NEWS THAT
YOU HAD A HEART ATTACK IN THE
LAST COUPLE OF DAYS AND IS BAD.
YOU ARE NOT LEAVING HERE.
>> THAT, JUST DAYS AFTER A
THREE HOUR BIKE RIDE AND A RUN
ON THE TREADMILL, WHICH WAS CUT
SHORT FROM THE PAIN.
>> WHO KNOWS WHAT COULD HAVE
HAPPENED.
IT EASILY COULD HAVE GONE IN
ANOTHER DIRECTION.
>> HE ADMITS THAT DURING THE
WORKOUT DAYS PRIOR HE BRUSHED
OFF SOME OF THE WARNING SIGNS.
CHEST PAINS, PAIN IN HIS ARMS
IN HIS JAW WALKING.
>> I SEARCH FOR IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO HAVE A HEART ATTACK SO IT
HAS TO BE SOMETHING ELSE AND
THAT IS WHY I IGNORED IT.
IT COULD NOT BE TRUE.
>> THE ENDURANCE ATHLETE IS
ALWAYS ON THE MOVE, EVEN DURING
A LONG DISTANCE CYCLING TRIP TO
THE MOUNTAINS MONTHS PRIOR, HE
FELT OKAY.
>> THEY BASICALLY SAID, IF YOU
HAVE NOT LIVED THE HEALTHY
LIFESTYLE YOU HAVE LIVED, YOU
CERTAINLY WOULD HAVE DIED.
>> NOW, WHILE HE CANNOT REVERSE
HIS GENETICS, HE IS WATCHING
WHAT HE EATS EVEN MORE CLOSELY.
IN CONTINUING A HEALTHY
LIFESTYLE WITHOUT FEAR.
>>Adrianna: COLORADO MAN SAID
THE LESSONS HE LEARNED FROM THE
CAT OWNER HELPED HIM TO THE
NORTH IN LINE WITH HIS BARE
HANDS.
>> FOR THE FIRST TIME, TRAVIS
IS TELLING HIS STORY ABOUT A
JOG TO THE MOUNTAINS TURNING
INTO A FIGHT FOR HIS LIFE.
>> I ENDED UP HEARING SOME PINE
NEEDLES RUSSELL, LIKE A STICK
BREAK.
I TURNED AROUND AND WAS PRETTY
BUMMED OUT TO SEE A MOUNTAIN
LION CHASING AFTER ME.
I STOPPED AND I THREW MY HANDS
UP IN THE AIR AND I STARTED
SHOUTING AND, IMPORTANTLY, THE
SHELLS DID NOT DETERIORATE.
SO IT JUST KIND OF KEPT RUNNING
AND LUNGED AT ME.
>> THE YOUNG MAN LINE WITH
ABOUT 50 POUNDS AND FOUR FEET
LONG WALKING ONTO HIS HANDS AND
WRIST AND CLAWING AT HIS FACE
AND NECK.
>> THAT IS WITH MY FEAR
RESPONSE TURNED INTO MORE OF A
FIGHT RESPONSE BECAUSE I
REALIZE HOW CLOSE IT WAS
GETTING TO MY EYES BUT.
>> THE 31-YEAR-OLD REFUSING TO
GIVE UP, STRIKING THE ANIMAL
WITH THE STICKS IN A LARGE
ROCK.
>> FORTUNATELY, I HAD A TOUGH
TIME SWINGING IT WITH MY ARM
WALKED IN THE CAT'S JAWS.
>> FINALLY GETTING THE UPPER
HAND.
>> A COUPLE OF MINUTES LATER IT
FINALLY STOPPED MOVING.
THEN THE JAWS OPENED AND I WAS
ABLE TO SCRIBBLE BACK UP THE
HILL AND GET THE HECK OUT OF
DODGE.
>> HE ENDED UP WITH NEARLY 30
STITCHES AND A REPUTATION
RIVALING CHUCK NORRIS.
>> CHUCK WOULD HAVE COME OUT
WITHOUT A SCRATCH.
YOU KNOW HIM.
>> WILDLIFE EXPERTS SAY HE DID
EVERYTHING RIGHT WHEN THE CAT
APPEARED.
THE ADVISEMENT DO NOT RUN.
RAISE YOUR ARMS TO LOOK BIGGER
AND FACE THE CAT AND TALK
FIRMLY.
IF IT ATTACKS THE FIGHT.
>>Adrianna: THAT WAS CLEAN SEND
OUT REPORTING THAT A CALIFORNIA
BOY WHO HAS A RARE MEDICAL
CONDITION IS THROAT AFTER
LIVING OUT HIS DREAM.
TAKE A LOOK HERE.
LEMUEL MILLER GREENFIELD HAS
ALWAYS WANTED TO BE A POLICE
OFFICER.
THE SACRAMENTO POLICE
DEPARTMENT GAVE HIM A SHOT.
HE GOT TO SPEND THE DAY AS AN
OFFICER AND HIS CLASSMATES SENT
HIM OFF IN STYLE.
>> HE ALWAYS HAS A POSITIVE
ATTITUD.
EVEN WHEN THINGS ARE ROUGH.
>> HE SEEMED TO LOVE IT.
WE WERE ALL TAKING PICTURES AND
HE WAS EXCITED.
>> AS WE ARE DRIVING HE IS
LEARNING HOW TO USE THE SIREN
IN PA SYSTEM.
WE ARE JUST HAPPY THAT WE CAN
MAKE HIS DAY.
>>Adrianna: ONCE MILLER ARRIVED
AT THE POLICE ACADEMY HE TOOK
PART IN TARGET PRACTICE AND HE
EVEN HANDCUFFED A SUSPECT WHO
WAS WANTED FOR STEALING DONUTS.
MAKE WHATEVER YOU ARE SNIFFING
AND OTHER DID FOR YOU FOR
VALENTINE'S DAY, IT WAS
PROBABLY NOT AS EXTREME AS WHAT
WE ARE ABOUT TO SHOW YOU.
CONNIE WEST SUPPRESSING HIS
WIFE WITH A ROOM FULL OF ROSES
AND KENNY G. THE SAXOPHONIST
WAS THERE TO SENATE COMPRESSION
WEST AND SHE POSTED THIS VIDEO
AND A PICTURE TO HER TWITTER
PAGE YESTERDAY SAYING, BEST
HUSBAND AWARD GOES TO MINE.
MOST THOUGHTFUL GIFTS EVER.
>>> A CLASSIC VIDEO GAMES
SETTING A NEW WORLD RECORD
PRICE WITH A MINT CONDITION
COPY OF THE ORIGINAL SUPER
MARIO BROTHERS HAS SOLD FOR
JUST OVER $100,000 AT AUCTION.
THE GAME WAS RELEASED BY
NINTENDO BACK IN 1985 AND THIS
COPYRIGHT HERE, HAS NEVER BEEN
OPENED.
>>Steve: PERIOD.
I HAD THAT GAME.
>>Adrianna: HOW MUCH CAN YOU
SELL IT FOR TODAY?
>>Steve: I DO NOT KNOW WHERE IT
IS.
>>Adrianna: IT IS WORTH
NOTHING.
>>Steve: I STOP ALL MY LEGOS.
THEY ARE WORTH A LOT.
WHEN ARE THEY VINTAGE LEGOS?
>>Steve: THEY ARE ORIGINALS.
HE GOOD STUFF.
I HAVE A WHOLE CITY.
>>> HERE IS OUR?
TOP THE WATERGATE HOTEL IN HERE
IS THE VIEW.
LOOKING TOWARD ROSLYN, THE
EVER-CHANGING SKYLINE, CITY
CENTER AND YOU CAN SEE, IS IT
CITY CENTER OR CENTER CITY?
>>Adrianna: CITY CENTER?
>>Steve: A LOT OF STORES AND
STUFF GOING ON THERE.
>>Adrianna: AND BARS.
>>Steve: EXACTLY.
OVER TOWARD OUR BUILDINGS HERE
AT ABC 7. LOOKING AT A FEW
PASSING CLOUDS BUT OTHERWISE A
NICE AMOUNT AFTERNOON SHAPING
UP FOR NOT ONLY THE DMV BUT FOR
THE MID ATLANTIC.
REAGAN NATIONAL AIRPORT AND A
LOT OF FOLKS ARE GETTING OUT
EARLY FOR THE LONG HOLIDAY
WEEKEND AND LOOKING GOOD FOR
YOUR TRAVEL PLANS.
AT LEAST FOR OF THE WEST COAST
BUT WE MIGHT RUN INTO PROBLEMS
IN THE MID PART OF THE COUNTRY
WITH WINTRY WEATHER.
HE BELIEVED WE ARE ALREADY
TALKING ABOUT OUR PAUL REPORT?
TREE POLLEN, IF YOU HAVE BEEN
SNIFFLING AND SNEEZING, AND ON
THE HIGH CATEGORY.
GRASPING NOT TO WORRY ABOUT,
PLEASE DELAY NOT AND MOLD IS IN
THE LOW CATEGORY WITH 60
DEGREES OF RECOGNITION, 59
WINCHESTER, 43 IN CUMBERLAND.
TO HAVE WINDS UPWARD OF 15 TO
20 MILES PER HOUR BUT A
TEMPERATURE CHANGE COMPARED TO
YESTERDAY AT THIS EXACT TIME
ABOUT 20 DEGREES WARMER.
I WILL NOT ARGUE WITH THAT.
FEBRUARY.
STORM WATCH 7 SATELLITE AND
RADAR WITHOUT A CLOUD COVER
MOVING IN FOR THE AFTERNOON
HOURS.
I SEE A FEW SPINDLES ALONG THE
MASON-DIXON LINE AND I DO NOT
ANTICIPATE THAT WILL AMOUNT TO
A LOT.
GOING OUT TO LUNCH ON THE SPOT?
LOOKING AT 60S AND GRABBED THE
SUNGLASSES AND A LIGHT JACKET
AND THAT IS ALL YOU NEED ADDED
CLOUD COVER FOR THIS EVENING
AND TEMPERATURES FALL TO THE
50S AND BY TONIGHT WE ARE
DROPPING INTO THE UPPER 20S TO
LOWER TO MIDDLE 30S AROUND 35
TO 38 DEGREES INSIDE THE
BELTWAY.
WITH THE COLDEST AIR ALONG THE
I-81 CORRIDOR.
TOMORROW, YOU HAVE HEARD A LOT
ABOUT THE POTENTIAL FOR A
LITTLE BIT OF WINTRY WEATHER.
WE WILL SEE MORE CLOUDS AND SUN
DURING THE FIRST HALF OF THE
DAY BUT THEN OUR SKIES WILL
BEGIN TO CLEAR.
AS THE SYSTEM MOVES OUT OF
HERE.
HERE IS OUR FUTURECAST THAT
WILL TAKE US TO THIS AFTERNOON,
THROUGH THE AFTERNOON HOURS AND
CALL DISCUSS ACROSS THE AREA.
WE ARE STILL DRY BUT THEN COME
EARLY TOMORROW MORNING WE ARE
WATCHING HIS SYSTEM THAT WILL
APPROACH FROM THE WEST BUT IT
IS A FRESHLY UPDATED FUTURECAST
WITHIN THE LAST 10 MINUTES BUT
NOTICE HOW IT KEEPS EVERYTHING
WILL GO TO THE SOUTH OF THE
.C. METRO AREA.SOUTH OF THE
THE SYSTEM KEEPS MOVING FURTHER
AND FURTHER SOUTH WHICH MEANS
LESS OF AN IMPACT ON THE METRO
IN TERMS OF ANY ACCUMULATION.
IF WE DO SEE ANY CUMULATING
SNOW IT WILL BE WET AND SLUSHY.
IT WILL NOT AMOUNT TO A WHOLE
LOT, MAINLY ON THE GRASSY
AREAS.
FOR THE DISTRICT, ARLINGTON AND
ALEXANDRIA, I DO NOT EXPECT
HARDLY ANYTHING AT ALL.
BUT THEN GO TO SOUTHERN
MARYLAND AND OVER TOWARD THE
CITY AND FOR EXPORT AND MAYBE
AN INCH AT BEST.
IF EVEN THAT.
HE MIGHT HAVE TO LOWER IT EVEN
MORE BUT HERE IS OUR FORECAST
FOR THE NEXT SEVEN DAYS WITH
THE WINTRY MIX FOR TOMORROW AND
THE SAME AS WE HEAD INTO THE
DAY ON SUNDAY.
AS WE MOVE INTO PRESIDENT'S DAY
IT IS DRY WITH TEMPERATURES IN
THE UPPER 40S.
OUR NEXT BIG WEATHER MAKER FOR
THIS WEEKEND APPEARS TO BE THE
MIDDLE OF THE UPCOMING WEEK.
LOOKING AT TEMPERATURES THAT
WILL GO FROM THE MID-30S TO THE
50 DEGREES RANGE.
WE COULD BE LOOKING AT WINTRY
WEATHER BY WEDNESDAY.
THE EVER-CHANGING FORECAST FOR
THE WEEKEND, COMPARED TO WHAT
WE THOUGHT A FEW DAYS AGO, IS
SHAPING UP TO BE A LOT BETTER
THAN ANTICIPATED.
>>Adrianna: WE WILL TAKE IT.
THANK YOU STEVE.
>>> FACEBOOK TURNED 15 THIS
WEEK BUT MANY ARE NOT
CELEBRATING.
SPECIAL THOSE WHO FELL VICTIM
TO ONE OF THE MOST SUCCESSFUL
SCAMS SO FAR THIS YEAR.
CONSUMER REPORTER JOHN MURRAY
SHOWS US WHAT IT IS SO EASY TO
FALL FOR THIS SO YOU DO NOT
WASTE YOUR MONEY.
>> PEOPLE ALL OVER THE D.C.
AREA AND ELSEWHERE ARE FALLING
FOR THE FACEBOOK GRANT SCAM.
WITH THIS AND MONEY TRYING TO
GET A NONEXISTENT GOVERNMENT
GRANT.
WHAT IS THE SCAMS SO
SUCCESSFUL?
BECAUSE IT INVOLVES ONE OF YOUR
BEST FRIENDS AS ONE VICTIM
FOUND OUT.
>> BEVERLY AND JENNIFER HAVE
BEEN FRIENDS FOREVER.
SO WHEN BEV SENT JENNIFER A
FACEBOOK MESSAGE SAYING SHE
JUST RECEIVED A BIG GOVERNMENT
GRANT.
>> HOW MUCH MONEY DID SHE SAY
SHE GOT?
>> $50,000.
>> JENNIFER WANT TO KNOW IF SHE
COULD APPLY TO.
>> SHE SAID TO CHECK INTO IT
BECAUSE THERE IS A POSSIBILITY
THAT I COULD GET IT.
>> JENNIFER, COPING WITH HEALTH
AND MONEY PROBLEMS CONTACT THE
GRANT AGENT AND SHE LEARNED
THAT SHE TO QUALIFIED FOR MONEY
IF SHE JUST PAID AN UPFRONT FEE
OF --
>> $700.
>> TRUSTING HER FRIEND SHE
DECIDED TO SEND IT IN IN DOING
SO SHE BECAME THE LATEST VICTIM
OF THE FACEBOOK GRANT SCAM.
SIMILAR CASES THE SCAM VICTIM
SINCE GIFT CARDS AND THE MONEY
IS LOST FOREVER.
BUT IN THIS CASE JENNIFER WENT
TO HER BANK AND SENT THE MONEY
THROUGH WESTERN UNION SO AT
LEAST THERE WAS A PAPER TRAIL.
>> ARE READ INTO HER FRIDAY
NIGHT.
>> SHE ASKED ABOUT THE
MESSAGES.> YOU WERE TELLING
ME THAT HE GOT A $50,000 GRANT.
FROM A CERTAIN PLACE.
AND SHE SAID, THAT WAS NOT ME.
AND I SIT HERE IS A PICTURE OF
YOU.
>> YOU DO NOT SEND ANY THOSE
MESSAGES,
>> NONE OF THEM.
NO.
NONE OF THEM.
NOT A ONE.
>> OUR FACEBOOK PAGE HAD BEEN
I wanted more from
my COPD medicine...
...that's why I've got the Power
of 1-2-3 medicines with TRELEGY.
The only FDA-approved
3-in-1 COPD treatment.
♪ TRELEGY. The Power of 1-2-3 ♪
♪ TRELEGY 1-2-3 TRELEGY ♪
With TRELEGY and the Power of
1-2-3, I'm breathing better.
TRELEGY works 3 ways to...
...open airways,...
...keep them open...
...and reduce inflammation...
...for 24 hours
of better breathing.
TRELEGY won't replace
a rescue inhaler
for sudden breathing problems.
TRELEGY is NOT for asthma.
Tell your doctor if you
have a heart condition
or high blood pressure
before taking it.
Do not take TRELEGY
more than prescribed.
TRELEGY may increase your
risk of thrush, pneumonia,
and osteoporosis.
Call your doctor if worsened
breathing, chest pain,
mouth or tongue swelling,..
...problems urinating, vision
changes, or eye pain occur.
Think your COPD
medicine is doing enough?
Maybe you should think again.
Ask your doctor about once-daily
TRELEGY and the
Power of 1-2-3.
♪ TRELEGY 1-2-3 ♪
Save at TRELEGY.com.
>>Adrianna: THE MUELLER PROBE
HAS STACKED OF INDICTMENTS AND
CONVICTIONS IN TRUMP SKIPPING
AND INNER-CIRCLE.
IS THERE ANOTHER ANGLE TO THE
STORE YOU HAVE NOT HEARD ABOUT?
FULL MEASURE CHERYL ATKINSON
JOINS US NOW AND IS GOOD TO
TALK TO YOU.
THIS DEALS WITH SOME IN OUR
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY.
TELL US ABOUT IT.
>> WE HAVE SPENT A LOT OF
ATTENTION ON THE MUELLER PROBE
AND SO FAR NO PUBLIC EVIDENCE
OF INVOLVEMENT BETWEEN
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND RUSSIAN
PRESIDENT PUTIN AS WAS ALLEGED.
THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF EVIDENCE
OVER THE PAST TWO YEARS THAT
HAS COME OUT ABOUT ALLEGED
SURVEILLANCE ABUSES COMMITTED
BY SOME INSIDE OUR INTELLIGENCE
COMMUNITY.
NOT JUST 2016 BUT IN THE DECADE
AND AND A HALF+ BEFORE THAT.
WE WILL GO OVER THE EVIDENCE
AND LOOK AT THE PART OF THE
STORE IN OUR COVER STORY THIS
WEEK.
>>Adrianna: LOOKING FORWARD TO
IT.
ALSO THIS WEEK, A TRIP TO A
WHIMSICAL TIKI BAR IN MONTANA.
WHAT MAKES THIS SO UNIQUE?
>> WHILE WE WERE IN MONTANA
SHOOTING IS FOR ON THEIR
HEALTHCARE SOLUTIONS, WE FOUND
A LITTLE TIKI BAR IN THE MIDDLE
OF SNOW IN MONTANA FOR THE
PATIENTS COME, BRING THEIR
FAMILIES AND SO ON.HEY HAVE
FOOD AND DRINK AND WATCH
MERMAIDS SWIMMING AROUND IN A
TANK UNDERGROUND THAT THEY CAN
SEE IN THE BAR.
WE CAN TALK YOU SEE WHAT
HAPPENS WHEN THE MERMAN, THE
MALE MERMAID GETS IN THE WATER
WITH HIS GIRLFRIEND AND HE WILL
HAVE FUN SEEING, IT IS A FAMILY
SHOW AND IS SOMETHING THE WHOLE
FAMILY CAN WATCH.
>>Adrianna: LOOKING FORWARD TO
IT.
THAN
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>Adrianna: MUST SEE VIDEO
RIGHT NOW.
YOU'VE SEEN HUGE VEGETABLES
BEFORE, BUT WHAT ABOUT THIS
HUMAN SIZED CABBAGE?
THIS AUSTRALIAN COUPLE GREW
THIS VEGGIE INTENSE MEDIA.
THEY MANAGED TO KEEP OUT THE
WALLABIES, POSSUMS, SLUGS AND
BUTTERFLIES WITH WIRE FENCING
AND A FINE NET.
THAT MASSIVE CABBAGE PRODUCED
TWO WEEKS OF COASTAL, SALADS
AND A TRADITIONAL GERMAN
CABBAGE DISH.
>>Steve: ONLY TWO WEEKS?
>>Adrianna: AND NO.
>>Steve: MY GOODNESS.
CRAZY STUFF IN TASMANIA.
>>> OUR WEATHER FORECAST
LOOKING REALLY FANTASTIC.
SHOULD'VE OF THE TEMPERATURE TO
65 AND MAYBE 66 DEGREES BECAUSE
PARTS OF THE AREA WILL SEE
TEMPERATURES THAT FORM BUT A
COLD FRONT LATER TODAY WILL
DROP OUR TIMBERS OVERNIGHT IN A
CHILLY DAY TOMORROW.
ESPECIALLY COMPARED TO THE
TODAY WITH A BETTER CHANCE OF
WINTRY MIX AS YOU MOVE INTO
TOMORROW MORNING.
MINUTES OUT OF TOWN.
REALLY SOUTH OF THE D.C. AREA.
THIS POINT IT DOES NOT LOOK
LIKE IT WILL BE A WHOLE LOT FOR
ARTS.
A FEW CHANCE FOR SHOWERS MAYBE
A FEW SNOWFLAKES MOVING INTO
SUNDAY.RESIDENT'S DAY IS DRY
WITH UPPER 40S AND COOLER ON
TUESDAY.
THAT IS GOING TO SET THE STAGE
FOR POTENTIALLY WINTRY WEATHER
ALONG THE METRO AREA BY
WEDNESDAY OF NEXT WEEK WITH
TEMPERATURES IN THE 30S.
THE EVER-CHANGING FORECAST, WE
WILL KEEP YOU UPDATED ON WJLA
24/7 THIS AFTERNOON AND BILL
KELLY WILL BE IN AT 4:00 AND WE
WILL GIVE YOU A FRESH LOOK AT
THE FORECAST.
OUR FUTURECAST IS ALWAYS
UPDATING AND THE LATEST WHEN
THEY CAME IN HOUSES SYSTEM EVEN
FURT
[ MUSIC PLAYING ]
>>> HELLO, EVERYONE, WELCOME TO
"AMANPOUR AND COMPANY."
HERE'S WHAT'S COMING UP.
>> TREMENDOUS NUMBERS DON'T LIE
>> THE PRESIDENT AND THE
POTENTIAL 2020 RIVALS TAKE TO
TEXAS.
THOUSANDS OF MILES AWAY,
CONGRESS APPEARS TO COMPROMISE
ON THE KEEPING THE GOVERNMENT
OPENED.
WE GET THE BORDER STORY FROM THE
REPUBLICAN MAYOR OF EL PASO AND
THE HUMANITARIAN FACE OF
IMMIGRATION FROM THOSE CLOSEST
TO HIM.
>>> PLUS, FEARS OF BIG BROTHER
THE FORMER HOMELAND SECURITY ON
THE DANGERS OF GOVERNMENT UNDER
SURVEILLANCE FROM CHINA TO
AMERICA.
WHEN BAE COLEMAN'S CAREER BEGAN,
SHE DIDN'T NOW KNOW HER COOKBOOK
WOULD MAKE IT TO UNIWORLD.
HER CUISINE IS SERVED THROUGH
EUROPE, ASIA, INDIA AND EUROPE,
ACCORDING TO BAE, TO TRAVEL IS
TO EAT.
>>> WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM,
EVERYONE, I'M CHRISTIANE
AMANPOUR IN LONDON.
PRSIDENT TRUMP SAYS HE'S NOT
SATISFIED WITH THE CONGRESSIONAL
BREAK THROUGH TO KEEP THE
GOVERNMENT OPENED.
HOUSE AND SENATE LEADERS ARE
GIVING THE PRESIDENT SOME FUNDS
FOR BORDER BARRIERS, NOT THE
$5.7 BILLION HE IS DEMANDING.
SPEAKING IN THE CABINET ROOM HE
SAID HE DIDN'T EXPECT ANOTHER
SHUTDOWN, ALSO HE SAID THIS.
>> SO I CAN TELL YOU AM I HAPPY
AT FIRST GLANCE?
I JUST GOT TO SEE IT.
THE ANSWER IS, NO, I'M NOT.
I'M NOT HAPPY.
BUT AM I HAPPY WITH WHERE WE'RE
GOING?
I'LL THRILLED.
BECAUSE WE ARE SUPPLEMENTING
THINGS AND MOVING THINGS AROUND
AND WE'RE DOING THINGS THAT ARE
FANTASTIC AND TAKING FROM FAR
LESS REALLY FROM FAR LESS
IMPORTANT AREAS.
>> SO WHILE NEGOTIATORS WERE
WORKING ON THE DEAL IN
WASHINGTON.
THE PRESIDENT WAS IN EL PASO,
TEXAS LAST NIGHT ON THE BODER
RALLYING HIS WALL-LOVING BASE.
HE ALSO HAD ONE EYE ON THE
DEMOCRATS BETO O'ROURKE.
HE RAN FOR SENATE IN 2018 AND
MIGHT RUN FOR PRESIDENT IN 2020.
AS A CONGRESSMAN, HE REPRESENTED
EMPASS SO.
>> THE PRESIDENT DESCRIBES
MEXICAN IMMIGRANTS AS RAPISTS
AND CRIMINALS.
WE HAVE THE CHANCE TO TELL HIM
AND THE COUNTRY, IMMIGRANTS
COMMIT CRIMES, INCLUDING VIOLENT
CRIMES AT A LOWER RATE THAN DO
AMERICANS WHO WERE BORN IN THIS
COUNTRY EL PASO HAS BEEN THE
SAFEST CITY IN THE UNITED STATES
OF AMERICA, NOT INSPITE OF THE
FACT THAT WE ARE A CITY OF
IMMIGRANTS, BUT BECAUSE WE ARE A
CITY OF IMMIGRANTS.
>> EL PASO HAS BECOME A
TOUCHDOWN OF WALL POLITICS.
THE CITY OF MORE THAN 50 MILES
OF FENCING ALONG THE BORDER.
SO WHAT IS THE PROBLEM THERE,
THE MAYOR JOINS ME NOW.
MAYOR, WELL DOCK BA TO THE
PROGRAM.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT EL PASO WOULD HAVE BEEN
A TOUCHSTONE AS I SAID IN THIS
WHOLE POLITICAL DRAMA.
BEFORE WE GET TO THAT, CAN I ASK
YOU ABOUT THE NEWS, WHAT YOU
THINK ABOUT THE COMPROMISE DEAL
BEING ON BOARD SECURITY TO TRY
TO KEEP THE GOVERNMENT OPENED
AND AFLOAT?
>> I HAVEN'T REALLY SEEN
ANYTHING IN THE HEADLINES ON THE
NEWS ABOUT IT.
I DON'T KNOW ANY OF THE
SPECIFICS.
I'M PROBABLY NOT ALLOWED TO
COMMENT.
FROM MY TIME IN THE LEGISLATURE
I WOULD SAY INCREMENT AM MOVING
UP INCREMENTALLY IS THE WAY TO
DO IT.
ON THE EL PASO PORTRAYERS, THERE
WERE NO WINNERS.
>> YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
WE SPENT MANY OF THOSE 35 DAYS
OF GOVERNMENT CLOSURE TALKING TO
SO MANY PEOPLE, FURLOUGHED
FEDERAL WORKERS.
SO MANY PEOPLE WHO HAD SUCH A
HARD TIME GETTING THROUGH AND
SURVIVING THIS SHUTDOWN.
I GUESS YOU ARE SITTING THERE AT
THE NEXUS OF THE GREAT POLITICAL
DRAMA OF OUR TIME.
SO WHEN YOU HAD THE PRESIDENT
AND A POTENTIAL 2020 RIVAL THERE
RALLYING LAST NIGHT.
WHAT DID YOU HEAR?
WHAT DID YOU TAKE AWAY FROM
EVERYTHING THAT WAS SAID?
>> I'M NOT SURE THERE WERE ANY
REVELATIONS FROM THE COMMENTS OF
EITHER BETO OR THE PRESIDENT.
I WAS TRYING TO PERSONALLY MEET
WITH THE PRESIDENT BEFOREHAND TO
VISIT WITH HIM.
BECAUSE I'VE SAID FOR MONTHS
THAT IF YOU WANT TO UNDERSTAND
THE BORDER, AND HOW YOU WORK
WITH MEXICO, YOU NEED TO COME TO
THE LARGEST CITY ON THE MEXICO
BORDER THAT HAS BEEN INTERTWINED
FOR ALMOST 400 YEARS, WE
UNDERSTAND IT BETTER, WE'RE THE
PLACE YOU OUGHT TO BE COMING TO
TALK ABOUT IT.
>> AND YET, DID YOU ACTUALLY MAN
TO SAY THAT TO HIM?
DID YOU MEET HIM?
>> I GOT A HANDSHAKE.
THAT WAS THE EXTENT OF IT.
WE THOUGHT WE WOULD GET MORE
TIME.
THAT WAS TRULY THE EXTENT OF IT.
>> DIFEEL HE WAS NOT TRYING TO
MEET YOU.
HE KNOWS YOU DISAGREE, HAVE YOU
DIFFERENT FACTS AT YOUR DISPOSAL
THAN HE TALKS ABOUT?
I MEAN, DID YOU FEEL IT WAS
DELIBERATE, HE DIDN'T WANT TO
MAKE TIME FOR YOU BECAUSE OF
WHAT YOU SAID?
LET'S PLAY WHAT HE'S ACTUALLY
SAID ABOUT YOU.
>> AND THERE IS NO PLACE BETTER
TO TALK ABOUT BORDER SECURITY,
WHETHER THEY LIKE IT OR NOT,
BECAUSE I HAVE BEEN HEARING A
LOT OF THINGS, OH THE WALL WON'T
MAKE THAT MUCH OF A DIFFERENCE?
YOU KNOW WHERE IT MADE A
DIFFERENCE?
RIGHT HERE IN EL PASO.
I DON'T CARE WHETHER THE SMAR A
REPUBLICAN OR A DEMOCRAT,
THEY'RE NUMBER OF CRAP WHEN THEY
SAY IT HASN'T MADE A BIG
DIFFERENCE.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL HEARING THAT?
WHAT WOULD YOU ANSWER BE TO
THAT?
>> I LOVE TO HEAR THAT OVER AND
OVER.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS, I'VE NEVER
BEEN AGAINST A PHYSICAL BARRIER
ON THE BORDER.
I THINK THAT'S PART AND PARCEL
TO AN ENTIRE PROCESS.
FROM A STRATEGY STAND POINT IS,
WE'RE IN CONTROL OF THE BORDERS,
WE'RE A SOVEREIGN NATION.
I'VE NEVER DISAGREED WITH THE
PRESIDENT ON THAT, ALL I'VE
TRIED TO DO IS CLARIFY HIS
COMMENTS THAT WE WERE NOT A
LAWLESS COMMUNITY WITH HIGH
CRIME RATES BEFORE THE FENCE
WENT UP UNDER THE BUSH
PRESIDENCY IN 2008.
CERTAINLY IT IS A CONTRIBUTING
FACTOR TOWARDS, TO OUR SAFETY
HERE, BUT IT IS -- IT WAS NOT
THE SOLE PANACEA PRIOR TO,
THAT'S ALL I'VE TRIED TO SAY.
I'VE NOT SPOKEN AGAINST PHYSICAL
BARRIERS OF ANY TYPE.
I THINK THAT'S A PART OF THAT
WHOLE PROCESS.
YOU MENTIONED EARLIER THERE IS
78 MILES OF FENCE IN THE EL PASO
SECTOR FOR THE BORDER CONTROL.
IT'S NOT CONTINUOUS.
A GROUP OF THE FENCING THAT WENT
UP UNDER THE BUSH ADMINISTRATION
IN 2008 WAS PRIMARILY A
REPLACEMENT OF ABOUT TEN MILES
OF CHAIN LINK THAT HAD HOLES IN
IT AND WITH FORESTS.
SO REALLY TO MY KNOWLEDGE, IT
WASN'T EXPANDING THE FENCING.
IT WAS MERELY IMPROVING IT.
>> AND TO YOUR POINT, I DO WANT
TO DIG DOWN, IT IS WORTH
CONSTANTLY PUTTING THE FACTS OUT
THERE ON THE CRIME FIGURES ON
WHAT THE BALL U WALL DID OR
DIDN'T DO AND HOW YOU RESPOND TO
THEM.
IT WAS INTERESTING, BETO
O'ROURKE TALKS ABOUT IT BEING
ONE OF THE SAFEST SECTORS.
IN CALIFORNIA, ALONG THE BORDER,
SORT OF MAKING A POINT THAT
ACTUALLY MANY OF THE CITIES
ALONG THE BORDER ARE SAFER THAN
THOSE FURTHER INLAND.
WOULD YOU AGREE WITH THAT?
>> WELL, FROM OUR STANDPOINT,
YES, FROM WHAT I UNDERSTAND,
EL PASO IS RANKED THE SAFEST
CITY.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO UNIFORM
CRIME STATISTICS REPORTED FROM
THE FBI OR TO THE FBI.
SO A LOT OF THAT HAS TO DO WITH
OUR POLICE FORCE AND OUR
COMMUNITY POLICING AND THE
THINGS THAT WE HAVE BEEN DOING
FOR MANY YEARS.
BUT THE ISSUE IS RELATED TO
VIOLENCE WHEN IT CAME TO OUR
REGION HAD TO DO WITH WHAT IS
WITH THE DRUG CARTELS WHEN THEY
WERE FIGHTING IT OUT A FEW YEARS
AGO.
IT NEVER CAME OVER TO EL PASS SO
WE HAVE A SIGNIFICANT LAW
ENFORCEMENT PRESENCE HERE.
PLUS WE HAVE A LARGE MILITARY
PRESENCE.
>> I WANT TO PUT UP THE GRAPH
RIGHT NOW TO TELL PEOPLE WHAT
YOU HAVE BEEN SAYING IN TERMS OF
THE SPIKE IN CRIME AND THE
TROUGH IN CRIME.
SO WE SEE IT WAS VERY HIGH CRIME
RATES IN THE EARLY '90s.
THEN IT STARTED TO DRAMATICALLY
OR DID DRAMATICALLY DROP OFF IN
2006 AND IT STAYED PRETTY LOW
AND THE WALL WAS BUILT AROUND
2008 AND IT WENT UP A BIT.
THE CRIME.
IT PRETTY MUCH STAYED PRETTY
LOW.
SO BASICALLY WHAT YOU ARE SAYING
AND THE GRASS SHOW AND THE FACTS
AND THE NU
EL PASO WAS GETTING SAFER AND
SAFER AND LESS AND LESS CRIME T
PREFER TO USE THE NOMENCLATURE
FENCE, IN CERTAIN NEIGHBORHOODS
FROM AN ANECDOTAL STANDPOINT,
THE RESIDENTS FEEL SAFE BECAUSE
OF THAT.
IT DID THE MOST DRAMATIC DROP IN
OUR CRIME RATE HAD TO OCCUR WITH
AUTOMOBILE THEFTS DURING THAT
TIME FRAME.
SO YOU DON'T HAVE THAT AS A
NUMBER BROKEN OUT.
BUT I'VE SEEN THAT.
BECAUSE WE HAD THE POOREST HOLES
IN THE CHAIN LINK FENCE WERE
COMING OVER, STEALING VEHICLES,
DRIVING THEM BACK TO JUAREZ AND
THAT FENCE HAD A SIGNIFICANT
IMPACT ON THAT SO I'VE SAID FROM
DAY ONE IT HAD AN IMPACT ON
CRIME.
IT HAD AN IMPACT ON THE FEELINGS
OF SECURITY IN CERTAIN
NEIGHBORHOODS.
BUT OVERALL THE CRIME RATE WOULD
NOT DRAMATICALLY DROP.
I FEEL LIKE MY JOB AS A MAYOR IS
TO EXPLAIN TO PEOPLE OUTSIDE
THAT WE WERE NOT LAWLESS CRIME
RIDDEN CITY BEFORE THE FENCE
CAME IN.
EL PASO IS A VIABLE COMMUNITY.
IT'S THE SIXTH LARGEST CITY IN
THE STATE OF TEXAS AND THE 19th
LARGEST CITY IN THE UNITED
STATES.
WE'RE A MAJOR PLAYER AND THE
REST OF THE WORLD NEEDS TO
UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> SO YOU JUST SAID, I DON'T
KNOW WHETHER YOU TERM IT A PETTY
CRIME OR NON-DRUG-RELATED CRIME
AND NON-VIOLENT CRIME.
YOU TALK ABOUT HOW IT STOPS SOME
AUTO THEFT AND PERHAPS PROPERTY
CRIMES AS WELL, SO THERE WAS
THAT POSITIVE AS PICTURE TO THE
FENCE.
BUT ON THE ISSUES THAT THE
PRESIDENT TALKS ABOUT, WHETHER
IT'S ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION WHETHER
IT'S DRUGS, YOU KNOW, HE'S
CONJURED UP YOU KNOW HOARDS OF
RACISTS AND MURDERS COMING OVER,
IT HAVEN HAD AN EFFECT, RIGHT
THE WALL?
IS THERE THAT CRISIS I GUESS I'M
TRYING TO SAY AT EL PASO AT THE
BORDER.
>>.
>> WELL, LET ME STATE THE
PHYSICAL BARRIERS, ACCORDING TO
CUSTOMS AND BORDER PROTECTION
AND THE POLICE DO CHANNEL PEOPLE
AND DRUG IN CERTAIN AREAS.
MOST OF THE DRUGS THAT ARE
PICKED UP ILLEGALLY COME THROUGH
OUR PORTS OF ENTRY.
SO A PHYSICAL BARRIER CHANNEL
PEOPLE IN A CERTAIN WAY.
BUT THEY'RE NOT THE TOTAL
RESOLUTION TO BORDER SECURITY.
WHICH NOBODY SEEMS TO FULLY
DEFINE ANYWAY OUT OF WALK.
BUT IF YOU LOOK AT THE GEOGRAPHY
OF TEXAS FROM EL PASO TO
BROWNSVILLE, IT'S ALMOST A
PHYSICAL IMPOSSIBILITY TO PUT A
FENCE FROM EL PASO TO
BROWNSVILLE.
YOU CAN PUT IT IN CERTAIN SPOTS.
BUT THE MAJORITY OF TEXAS IS
PRIVATE LAND.
>> THAT WON'T WORK.
YOU NEED MORE MAN POWER,
TECHNOLOGY, A COMBINATION OF ALL
OF THE ABOVE.
I WOULD RELY ON THE EXPERT THAT
BORDERLAND AND HOMELAND SECURITY
TO TELL US WHAT THEY REALLY
NEED.
>> DO YOU?
YOU SORT OF INTIMATED THAT
PERHAPS THOSE IN WASHINGTON ARE
NOT QUITE CLEAR ABOUT THE
PARAMETERS OF WHAT THEY SEEM TO
BE TALKING ABOUT.
WERE YOU SURPRISED WHEN THE
PRESIDENT, WE UNDERSTAND, DID
OFF SCRIPT AND AD LIBBED ABOUT
LOVING AND WANTING MORE LEGAL
IMMIGRATION INTO THE UNITED
STATES?
WHEN HE SAID THAT AND WHEN YOU
WERE LISTENING TO THE SPEECH,
WHAT DID YOU THINK?
>> WELL, I DO THINK THAT THAT IS
SOMETHING THAT NEEDS TO BE DONE.
I THINK THAT LOTTERY SYSTEM IS
NOT FUNCTIONING AT ALL.
MY FORMER FIRM WAS TRYING TO
BRING IN AN UNDERWRITER FROM
LOIDS OF LONDON FOR SEVERAL
YEARS AND THE LOTTERY SYSTEM
THEY LOCKED OUT EVERY YEAR FOR
THREE YEARS AND GAVE UP.
BUT WHEN WE'RE BELOW 4%
UNEMPLOYMENT, WE'VE GOT TO DO
SOMETHING MORE ON LEGAL
IMMIGRATION AND I'VE ALSO SAID
IF YOU ARE A DACA OR A DREAMER
AND YOU SERVE IN THE MILITARY,
IT OUGHT TO BE AUTOMATIC YOU GET
U.S. CITIZENSHIP IF YOU SO
DESIRE AND FOR THE OTHERS AS
WELL.
IF YOU ARE ALREADY HERE AND THAT
10 TO 12 MILLION GROUP THAT'S
HERE UNDER FALSE SOCIAL SECURITY
NUMBERS, BUT EARNING A LIVING
AND RAISING THEIR FAMILY AND NOT
INVOLVED IN ANY CRIMINAL
ACTIVITIES.
YOU BET THOSE PEOPLE AND YOU
GIVE THEM GREEN CARDS, SO THAT
THEY CAN HAVE LEGAL WAYS OF
PAYING TAXES AND FOUGHT JUST
BOGUS SOCIAL SECURED NUMBERS AND
ANYBODY THAT DOESN'T PASS A
CRIMINAL BACKGROUND CHECK OUGHT
TO BE DEPORTED.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY WE WILL DEAL
WITH THAT I KNOW WE HAVE FOLKS
THAT SAY, OH, THEY'RE HERE
ILLEGALLY, WE CAN'T DEAL WITH
IT.
MY COMMENT IS THE EGG IS ALREADY
BROKEN, DEAL WITH IT.
>> WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID AD
LIBBED DURING THE STATE OF THE
UNION, DO YOU FEEL THAT WAS A
PART OF BE RIGHT BACKING BREAKI
THE EGG, IN OTHER WORDS MOVING
ALONG THE ROAD OF ACCEPTING WHAT
YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT, THAT
THERE NEEDS TO BE MORE LEGAL
IMMIGRATION AND PROPER
IMMIGRATION REFORM?
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS A UNIQUE
PERSONALITY WITHIN THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY.
HE'S THE PRESIDENT THAT WE'VE
NEVER SEEN BEFORE LIKE HIM HIM
I'M NOT SURE WE'LL SEE AFTER
HIM.
BUT HE IS IN A POSITION TO BE
ABLE TO DO SOME THINGS THAT I
THINK OTHERS MAY NOT HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO TO.
SO I WOULD HOPE HE WOULD MOVE
FORWARD WITH THAT.
HE'S INTIMATED ABOUT IMMIGRATION
REFORM AND OUR NATION NEEDS IT.
>> WELL, YOU ARE A POLITICIAN,
MAYOR.
AND YOU'VE ACCURATELY DESCRIBED
THE PRESIDENT.
HE'S A UNIQUE OPERATION IN THE
POLITICAL AFFIRMAMENT, BUT ONE
THAT MIGHT BE ABLE TO GET
CERTAIN THINGS DONE.
DO YOU SEE THAT HAPPENING AND
THE POSSIBILITY OF THAT
HAPPENING BY HIS HACKSS, BY HIS
POLIT
POLITICKING, ON IMMIGRATION, FOR
INSTANCE?
AS WE HAVE JUST BEEN DISCUSSING?
IN OTHER WORDS, DO YOU THINK HE
CAN DELIVER AS YOU HAVE
DESCRIBED?
>> I THINK IF HE WANTS TO, HE
CAN DELIVER.
YES.
SO IT'S UP TO HIM TO DETERMINE
THAT.
I WOULD BE HOPEFUL THAT HE
WOULD.
>> RIGHT.
SO LET'S ASK YOU AGAIN TO TALK
ABOUT THE REAL TRAGEDY THAT WE
SEE, WHICH IS A HUMAN TRAGEDY OF
ALL THIS CONFLATION OF ILLEGAL
AND ASYLUM AND THESE CHILDREN
AND FAMILIES BEING SEPARATED AT
THE BORDER AND THIS HORRENDOUS
SITUATION DOES NOT SEEM TO BE
GETTING ANY BETTER.
IN FACT, ESSENTIALLY THE WORSE
EWOULD LIKE TO PLEAS PLAY FOR
YOU THE DETENTION WHEN WE SPOKE
ACTUALLY BACK IN JUNE.
>> WE HAVE BEEN GIVEN NO
INFORMATION REGARDING THE
CHILDREN, WHERE THEY ARE.
ALL WE KNOW IS THEY ARE BEING
DISTRIBUTED THROUGHOUT THE
UNITED STATES, WHICH WAS A
SURPRISE TO COME OF US.
WE HEARD ABOUT THEM BEING PLACED
IN MICHIGAN, NEW YORK, RHODE
ISLAND, ELSEWHERE, THAT'S THE
REASON WE CAME TOGETHER AS A
GROUP OF MAYORS TO SAY ENOUGH IS
ENOUGH.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
THIS IS NOT WHAT WE ARE ABOUT AS
A NATION.
>> SO, MAYOR, THAT WAS IN JUNE,
HAVE THINGS GOTTEN BETTER NEAR
WHERE YOU ARE?
BECAUSE THERE ARE REPORTS THAT
ARE VERY, VERY UPSETTING TO
READ.
I WANT TO KNOW IN YOUR LOCATION,
HAVE THINGS GOTTEN BETTER?
>> THE NUMBERS ARE INCREASING.
WE'RE GETTING SOMEWHERE BETWEEN
3 AND 400 A DAY.
THESE ARE FAMILIES.
THEY'RE NOT BEING SEPARATED.
THE TORNEO SHELTER THAT WAS AT
THE TIME UP FOR UNACCOMPANIED
MINORS THAT I VISITED LAST
SUMMER WAS DISBANDED IF JANUARY.
AND THEY WENT OFF TO THEIR
SPONSORS.
AS I SAID, WE GET, THE WORD I
HAVE PER DAY IS ABOUT 3 TO 400.
THEY'RE PROCESSED THROUGH --
THEY COME INTO EMPASS SO ONCE
DISCHARGED FROM I.C.E. AND OUR
NGO, THE ENUNCIATION HOUSE HAS
APPROXIMATELY 20 SHELTERS IT
COORDINATES AND THEY ARE HERE,
FAMILIES TOGETHER.
THE PARENTS ARE GIVEN ANKLE
BRACELETS IN THE PROCESS AND
THEN THEY GO OFF TO THEIR
SPONSORS.
THEY HAVE BUS FARE, AIR FAIR,
WHATEVER IT IS THAT DOES THAT,
WHATEVER THEY NEED.
THEY'RE HERE USUALLY 24 TO A
MAXIMUM OF 48 HOURS, SOME AS
LONG AS 96 HOURS.
BUT I DON'T KNOW THAT YOUR
VIEWERS FULLY UNDERSTOOD WHEN
CPP, CPP IS A LAW ENFORCEMENT
AGENCY AND THE WAY IT WAS
STRUCTURED IS THAT HHS WOULD BE
THE ENTITY THAT WOULD BE
EQUIPPED TO TAKE CARE OF THOSE
THAT WERE HELD IN DETENTION AND
THEY'VE FIT DOING THAT.
I THINK THERE WAS A 9th CIRCUIT
COURT DECISION, AS I'M TOLD,
THAT SAYS CAN'T HOLD ANY
IMMIGRANTS THAT ARE SEEKING
ASYLUM LONGER THAN 20 DAYS.
SO THEY'RE PROCESSING THEM,
RELEASING THEM TO THEIR
SPONSORS.
>> SO YOU MENTIONED THE BOARD OF
PROTECTION UNIT AND I CONTRACTOR
AND THE LPG SERVICES.
WHAT DOES IT FEEL LIKE AS I LET
YOU GO'S MAYOR OF EL PASO THAT
YOUR CITY IS BEING REALLY A
PUNCHING BACK AND SORT OF IN THE
MIDDLE OF ALL OF THIS VERY, VERY
YOU KNOW HEATED POLITICS AND TO
AN EXTENT FAKE NEWS FOR A LONG
TIME.
>> WELL, I'M DOING MY BEST TO
TRY TO ARTICULATE THE CORRECT
STORY OF WHERE WE ARE AS WELL AS
EXPLAINING THAT WE ARE IN FAVOR
OF A SAFE BORDER AND THAT IS A
SOVEREIGN NATION AND YOU NEED TO
CONTROL OUR BORDERS, BUT THAT
EL PASO IS A VIABLE COMMUNITY, A
CONTRIBUTING COMMUNITY AND HAS A
CLOSE RELATIONSHIP BICULTURALLY
AND BINATIONALLY.
FAMILIES ON BOTH SIDE AND
COMMERCE WITH MEXICO.
I MEAN WE HAVE SIX BRIDGES THAT
HAVE 23,000 ILLEGAL PEDESTRIANS
COMING NORTH EVERY DAY.
I GOT 21 MILLION PRIVATE
PASSENGER VEHICLES THAT COME
NORTH ON AN ANNUAL BASIS.
WE GOT $82 BILLION OF TRADE
IMPORTS AND EXPORTS THAT GO
THROUGH HERE.
I MEAN WE'RE A MAJOR PLAYER AND
VERY MUCH INTERTWINED WITH
MEXICO, IF YOU WANT TO KNOW THE
BORDER, COME TO EMPASS SO.
>> ALL RIGHT MAYOR OF EMPASS SO,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR BEING
HERE WITH US.
>>> SO, WITH ALL THIS
POLITICKING, THERE ARE REAL
FLESH AND BLOOD PEOPLE WHO ARE
AFFECTED ON A DAILY BASIS.
THE MOST CONTROVERSIAL TRUMP
IMMIGRATION POLICY HAS NOT BEEN
THE WALL, BUT AS I MENTIONED
CHILD SEPARATION, DELIBERATELY
REMOVING MIGRANT CHILDREN FROM
THEIR PARENTS WHO ARE THEN
DETAINED.
A NEW INSPECTOR GENERAL REPORT
REVEALS THOUSANDS MORE WERE
SEPARATED FROM THEIR FAMILY
PREVIOUSLY ACKNOWLEDGED.
THE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND
HUMAN SERVICE FRS HAD TOO HOUSE
THE CHILDREN AND TESTIFYING ON
CAPITOL HILL RECENTLY COMMANDER
JONATHAN WHITE SAYS HE BELIEVES
THE POLICY HAD CATASTROPHIC
IMPLICATIONS.
>> SO THIS PROBLEM IS NOT OVER
EVEN AFTER THEY UNIFY THE CHILD
WITH THEIR FAMILY.
RIGHT?
>> THE CONSEQUENCES OF
SEPARATION FOR MANY CHILDREN
WILL BE LIFE LONG.
>> LET'S BE CLEAR IS THERE A
NULLIFICATION OF RETRAUMATIZE OR
IS THIS AN ADDITIONAL TRAUM THAT
ADDS ADDITIONAL STRESS AND
ADDITIONAL HARM TO A CHILD AFTER
THEY EXPERIENCE THE DIFFICULTIES
THAT THEY EXPERIENCED IN THEIR
HOME COUNTRY GOING THROUGH THE
LONG TREK?
DID HE ADD ADDITIONAL
RETRAUMIZATION TO THAT CHILD?
>> MANY CHILDREN THAT IS A ABLE
CONSEQUENCE, YES.
>> SO WE'RE GOING TO DIG DOWN
NOW INTO THE HUMANITY OF THAT
FACT AND THE LAW.
ED LAREN DARRAGH REPORTED
EXTENSIVELY ON THE BORDER AND
CHILD SEPARATION.
HE'S JOINING US FROM EL PASO.
MARY BOWER IS A DEPUTY DIRECTOR
FOR THE POVERTY LAW CENTER WHICH
REPRESENTS IMMIGRANTS IN
DETENTION.
SHE TRAVELED ALSO TO THE BORDER.
AND SHE IS JOINING US FROM
CHARLOTTESVILLE, VIRGINIA.
WELCOME TO YOU BOTH.
I JUST WANT TO ASK YOU, ED,
START OFF WITH SOME STORIES
ACTUALLY FROM BOTH OF YOU.
ED, YOU ARE THERE IN EL PASS SO
YOU JUST HEARD THE MAYOR.
TELL ME WHAT YOU HAVE SEEN AND
WHAT HAVE YOU REPORTED ON THE
HUMAN STORIES THAT IS BEHIND ALL
THESE POLITICS?
>>.
>> I THINK THE IMPORTANT THING
IS HOW FLUID THINGS CLANG ON THE
BORDER.
THE REASON WHY SOME PEOPLE MIGHT
TRY TO MIGRATE INTO THE UNITED
STATES IN 2018 AND 9019 IS BIFF
THAN THREE OR FOUR YEARS AGO.
>> THAT HAS BEEN THE CHALLENGE
WE HAVE SEEN HERE ALONG THE
U.S.-SOUTHERN BORDER OVER THE
COURSE OF THE LAST MONTH, WHERE
REALLY WE HAVE SEEN THE ARRIVAL
OF FAMILY UNITS, FAMILIES
ARRIVING WITH CHILDREN.
THAT IS A RELATIVELY NEW
PHENOMENON THAT YOU ARE SEEING
HERE ON THE U.S. SOUTHERN
BORDER.
BECAUSE OF THAT, THERE HAVE BEEN
SOME LAW MAKERS WHO HAVE
CRITICIZED THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION FOR NOT ADAPTING
QUICK ENOUGH TO DEALING WITH THE
SPECIFIC TYPE OF PEOPLE WHO ARE
ARRIVING HERE AT THE U.S.
SOUTHERN BORDER.
SO THAT'S WHY IT'S LED TO THIS
DRAMATIC INCREASE IN CHILDREN
SEPARATED FROM THEIR PARENTS.
IT WAS A PLAN THE ADMINISTRATION
HOPED A ZERO POLICY WOULD SERVE
AS A DETERRENT TO MIKE GRANTS
COMING MOSTLY FROM CENTRAL
AMERICAN COMPANIES TO DETER THEM
E THEM FROM COMING TO THE UNITED
STATES.
EVEN THOUGH THE ADMINISTRATION
SAYS THAT POLICY HAS BEEN
STOPPED, WE HEARD THE STORY OVER
HERE OVER THE COURSE OF A
MONTH-AND-A-HALF A YOUNG GIRL
SEPARATED FROM HER FATHER AT THE
END OF DECEMBER.
IT TOOK ALMOST A MONTH FOR THAT
GIRL TO BE REUNITED WITH HER
FAMILY.
THESE STORIES HAVE RAISED
QUESTIONS TO WHAT EXTENT THESE
CHILD SEPARATION CASES ARE STILL
UNFOLDING.
>> LET ME TURN TO YOU, MARY
BOWER, YOU DEAL WITH THIS FROM
YOUR LEGAL PERSPECTIVE.
THERE IS ALSO A HUMANITARIAN
PERSPECTIVE.
DESCRIBE THE EXTENT OF WHAT ARE
YOU SEEING IN.
THE SECRETARY GENERAL SAYS
THOUSANDS MORE HAVE BEEN
SEPARATED THAN EVER HAS BEEN
ACKNOWLEDGED.
IN OTHER WORDS THE PROBLEM IS
WORSE THAN WE THOUGHT IT WAS.
>> IT ABSOLUTELY IS WORSE.
WHAT WE SEE IS FAMILY SEPARATION
HAS EVOLVED.
IT'S TAKEN A SLIGHTLY DIFFERENT
FORM.
THERE ARE 10,000 KIDS DETAINED
NOW ACROSS THE UNITED STATES
BECAUSE OF A DELIBERATE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION POLICY AND IT'S
NOT AS THERE ARE THE PREVIOUS
SPEAKER INDICATED, A FAILURE TO
ADAPT.
IT IS A DELIBERATE AND NEFARIOUS
POLICY WHERE THE ADMINISTRATION
DECIDED THAT THEY WERE GOING TO
TAKE ACTIONS THAT WOULD RESULT
IN KIDS BEING DETAINED LONGER
AND IN PARENTS AND SPONSORS
BEING TURNED OVER TO
DEPORTATION.
THAT'S WHAT WE ARE SEEING.
WE ARE SEEING MORE THAN 10,000
KIDS LOCKED UP.
MOST WHO DON'T NEED TO BE LOCKED
UP.
>> JUST TO FOLLOW UP ON THAT,
NOW THAT WE KNOW MORE AND THIS
HAS BEEN THE CASE OF GREAT
CONTENTION AND ANGER IN THE
UNITED STATES AND ACTUALLY
AROUND THE WORLD.
ARE YOU ABLE TO DEEM WITH THESE?
ARE YOU ABLE TO HIGHLIGHT THESE
CASES?
IS THE LAW RESPONDING FAST
ENOUGH?
I MEAN, CAN YOU GET THEM
REUNITED WITH THEIR FAMILIES?
WHAT IS THE SITUATION ON THAT
LEVEL, MARY?
>> WELL, WE HAVE BROUGHT A CLASS
ACTION LAWSUIT ON BEHALF OF ALL
KIDS WHO ARE DETAINED ACROSS THE
UNITED STATES.
BUT WE KNOW THAT ANY CHILD WHO
IS LOCKED UP AND SEPARATED FROM
FAMILY IS EXPERIENCING A TRAUM.
WE KNOW THAT.
WE KNOW THESE KIDS WILL
EXPERIENCE LONG-TERM TRAUMA,
BECAUSE THEY ARE SEPARATED FROM
THEIR PARENTS SO WE'RE WORKING
TO REUNITE THEM AS QUICKLY AS
POSSIBLE.
BUT THIS DOES NOT HAVE TO BE.
THIS IS THE RESULT OF
CALCULATED, DELIBERATE
INTENTIONAL ACTS TO SEPARATE
KIDS FROM THEIR PARENTS AND TO
USE THE CHILDREN ESSENTIALLY AS
BAIT TO LURE THEIR PARENTS INTO
THE DEPORTATION SYSTEM AND
THAT'S WHAT WE ARE SEEING PLAY
OUT.
>> I'M GOING TO GET BACK TO THE
LEGAL REMEDY TO THIS I WANT TO
FOLLOW UP WITH ED ON YOU KNOW
YOU ARE SEEING EVERY DAY THESE
STORIES.
ED YOU HAVE BEEN SEEING THEM,
TOO, ON A REGULAR BASIS.
YOU HAVE BEEN REPORTING ON THEM.
GIVE ME A SENSE OF WHAT YOU SEE
THE KIDS THE FAMILIES, HOW
THEY'RE BEING AFFECTED THE
TRAUMAS.
>> Reporter: YEAH, I THINK A LOT
OF PEOPLE WHO ARRIVE AND I SPENT
A LOT OF TIME IN SHELTERS ON THE
MEXICAN SIDE OF THE BORDER,
THESE FAMILIES WHO HAVE MADE THE
LONG JOURNEY FROM THEIR CENTRAL
AMERICAN COUNTRY HOMES AND TO
GET THERE.
AND MANY TIMES WHEN I SPEAK TO
THEM, THEY KIND OF SEEM
OBLIVIOUS, NOT AWARE AS TO THE
EXTENT OF HOW MUCH THIS IS BEING
DEBATED HERE IN THE UNITED
STATES.
THE AMOUNT OF MISTAKES
INFORMATION THAT THEY'RE GIVEN E
GIVING IN THEIR HOME COUNTRIES
AND ESSENTIALLY LURED BY
CRIMINAL AND ORGANIZED GANGS
THAT BRING THEM THROUGH CENTRAL
AMERICA INTO MEXICO AND TRY TO
GET THEM INTO THE UNITED STATES.
THIS IS HUGE BUSINESS FOR A LOT
OF THESE SMUGGLERS THAT GET THEM
HERE TO THE DOORSTEP OF THE
UNITED STATES AND ESSENTIALLY
WASH THEIR HANDS OF THEM.
THEN IT BECOMES, YOU KNOW ARC
DANGEROUS SITUATION FOR THEM.
SO YOU SEE A LOST CONFUSION AND
BY AND LARGE, I HAVE SPOKEN TO
HUNDREDS, DOZENS OF THESE PEOPLE
OVER THE COURSE OF MY REPORTING
HERE AND ON THE U.S.-SOUTHERN
BORDER FOR YEARS AND ALL OF THEM
REPEATEDLY TELL YOU THAT THEY
COME HERE SIMPLY LOOKING FOR ATE
BER OPPORTUNITY AND IN A CASE
RECENTLY OF THE CENTRAL AMERICAN
MIGRANT, MANY OF THEM TRYING TO
ESCAPE VIOLENCE.
THEY HAVE BEEN DIRECTLY
THREATENED BY GANGS IN THEIR
HOMETOWN.
THEY FEEL LIKE THE ONLY COURSE
OF ACTION THEY HAVE IS TO DROP
EVERYTHING AND RUN NORTH.
>> MARY, FROM A LEGAL POINT OF
VIEW AND THE PERSPECTIVE ON THE
BIG PICTURE, THE PRESIDENT IS
OFTEN GOING TO THE BOARD IR,
GOING TO EL PASO THIS EVENING
AND TALKING ABOUT THE RACISTS
AND THE -- RAPISTS AND CRIMINALS
AND GANGS AND MS-13, ET CETERA.
SORT OF INVOKING YOUNG MEN,
MIDDLE AGED MEN ADOLESCENTS.
FIRST AND FOREMOST, WHO ARE THE
MAJORITY OF PEOPLE COMING OVER?
ARE THEY THAT DEMOGRAPHIC?
AND WHERE ARE MOST OF THE
ILLEGALS?
ARE THEY COMING THROUGH BORDER
THE SOUTHERN BORDER?
WHERE IS THE CENTER OF GRAVITY
ON THIS ISSUE?
>> THEY'RE NOT THE PEOPLE DONALD
TRUMP DESCRIBED, THEY'RE NOT
RAPISTS AND MURDERERS.
THE PEOPLE COMING TO UNITED
STATES WE ARE SEEING DEBORDEER
ARE DESPERATE PEOPLE TERRIFIED
AND FLEEING VIOLENCE.
THEY'RE COMING TO THE UNITED
STATES.
IN MANY CASES THEY WOULD LIKE TO
APPLY FOR ASYLUM AT THE PORT OF
ENTRY AND THEY CANNOT BECAUSE OF
ADMINISTRATION POLICIES.
WE SEE THAT IN TERMS OF THE
NUMBERS OF UNDOCUMENTED PEOPLE.
THE MAJORITY OF THE UNDOCUMENTED
PEOPLE IN THE UNITED STATES NOW
ARE ACTUALLY COMING IN THROUGH
AIRPORTS, PEOPLE OVERSTAYING
VISAS.
SO ALL OF THE RED RICK FROM
TRUMP ABOUT WHO IMMIGRANTS ARE
AND WHY THEY'RE COMING AND WHAT
THEY'RE SEEKING, IT'S JUST
WRONG.
IT'S JUST DEMONSTRABLY WRONG.
WE KNOW THAT WE KNOW IMMIGRANTS
ARE FAR LESS LIKELY TO COMMIT
CRIMES THAN U.S. CITIZENS.
WE KNOW ALL OF THAT.
>> WE HEARD BETO O'ROURKE SAY
THAT THE MAYOR OF EL PASO,
TEXAS, TALKING ABOUT HIS
PRACTICALLY CRIME-FREE LOCATION
THERE IN EL PASO.
CAN YOU JUST SEPARATE FOR US
WHAT APPEARS TO BE A CONSISTENT
CONFLATION OF THE ISSUES?
THERE'S LEGAL.
THEN THERE'S ILLEGAL.
THERE'S ASYLUM SEEKERS.
MARY, JUST TELL US, WHO EACH
GROUP IS AND HOW EACH NEEDS TO
BE DEALT WITH.
>> WELL, I THINK WE HAVE TO ACT
KNOWLEDGE FIRST THAT CONSTANT
RHETORIC ABOUT HOW HE WANTS
PEOPLE TO DO THINGS LEGALLY IS
ALSO DEMONSTRABLY WRONG.
RIGHT?
BECAUSE HE'S NOT ALLOWING PEOPLE
TO APPLY AT THE PORTS OF ENTRY.
HE IS PUTTING UP HUGE OBSTACLES
TO ALLOW PEOPLE TO APPLY FOR
ASYLUM TO BE ABLE TO DO THAT.
HE HAS TAKEN BASICALLY A MILLION
PEOPLE WHOARE HERE UNDOCUMENTED
AND TRIED TO MAKE THEM ILLEGAL
BY TRYING TO TERMINATE DACA AND
CPS.
HE HAS UNDERGONE POLICY AFTER
POLICY AFTER POLICY, THAT IS
DESIGNED TO ATTACK PEOPLE WHO
ARE HERE BOTH LAWFULLY AND
UNLAWFULLY AND TO ATTACK THE
SYSTEM OF IMMIGRATION AND ASYLUM
AT ITS ROOTS TO MAKE THAT
UNAVAILABLE TO PEOPLE.
SO WE KNOW THAT RHETORIC ABOUT
HOW PEOPLE NEED TO STAND IN LINE
OR HOW THEY NEED TO DO IT
LEGALLY.
>> THAT IS BELIED BY THE ACTIONS
OF ADMINISTRATION THIS
ADMINISTRATION.
THEY DON'T WANT PEOPLE TO DO
THAT THEY DON'T WANT IMMIGRATION
AT ALL.
THEY HAVE MADE THAT CLEAR
THROUGH THEIR POLICY.
YES, WE NEED TO HAVE AN
IMMIGRATION REFORM THAT LETS 11
MILLION OR SO HERE OUT OF
STATUS.
WE NEED TO HAVE THAT KIND OF
REFORM.
WE HAVE NEEDED THAT FOR WELL
OVER A DECADE OR TWO.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN THAT WE
PUT UP A WALL AND DENY THE
ABILITY TO APPLY ASYLUM TO
PEOPLE WHO ARE DESPERATE AND ON
OUR DOORSTEP.
WE ENACTED THE ASYLUM LAW IN THE
WAKE OF WORLD WAR II EXACTLY SO
THIS WOULD NOT HAPPEN AGAIN.
BECAUSE THE WEST WAS ASHAMED, IT
HAD TURNED AWAY JEWS DURING THE
HOLOCAUST.
WE SAID NEVER AGAIN WE DON'T
WANT TO TURN OUR BACK ON
DESPERATE PEOPLE AT OUR
DOORSTEP.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE ASYLUM LAWS
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
WE ARE SHAMEFULLY, SHAMEFULLY,
IGNORING OUR LEGAL MORAL
RESPONSIBILITY HERE.
>> LET ME ASK YOU TO STAND ON
THAT, YOU SEE IT, YOU REPORT ON
THE PEOPLE.
AND THERE IS THIS POLICY THAT
THE PRESIDENT INPLEMTED CALLED
METERING WHICH LIMITS THE NUMBER
OF ASYLUM SPEAKERS ALLOWED TO
ENTER THE UNITED STATES EACH DAY
AND THEY ARE HELD IN DETENTION
CENTERS OR CENTRES ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE BORDER.
MEANING THEY HAVE TO WAIT MONTH
TO MONTH FOR THEIR CLAIMS ARE
PROCESSED.
WHAT IS THAT DOING AT THE
BOARDER?
THE PRESIDENT CLAIMS A CRISIS AT
THE BORDER.
IS THIS A PART, ED, OF THE
CRISIS?
IS IT MANUFACTURING A CRISIS, IF
YOU LIKE?
>> Reporter: I THINK, MARY
BRINGS UP AN IMPORTANT POINT YOU
GUYS ARE HITTING ON.
THAT'S THE NEWEST ANGLE OF WHAT
WE ARE SEEING IN OUR REPORTING
ALONG THE U.S.-SOUTHERN BORDER.
RIGHT NOW MENTIONED THIS
METERING SYSTEM.
SO PEOPLE UNDERSTAND WHAT IT'S
LIKE.
IMAGINE A GROUP, VERY LARGE
GROUPS SHOWING UP IN VARIOUS
SECTION OF THE U.S. SOUTHERN
BORDER.
IT'S NOT UNCOMMON TO SEE 200,
300 MIKE GRANTS SHOW UP IN A
BORDER TOWN IN A REMOTE AREA AND
THEY COME TO JUAREZ, FOR
EXAMPLE, THEY'RE AT THE PORT OF
ENTRY, THEN THE U.S. MIGHT HAVE
A SYSTEM IN PLACE, I THINK IT
VARIES BETWEEN WHICH PORT OF
ENTRY YOU COME INTO.
TODAY THEY SAY WE WILL TAKE 15
ASYLUM SEEK ESSER, TODAY 12 THE
DAY BEFORE NINE.
THAT'S NOT LETTING EVERYBODY
COME IN.
THAT'S FORCING PEOPLE TO WHITE
ON THE MEXICAN SIDE OF THE
BORDER AND THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION IS ALSO FLIRTING
WITH THE IDEA, I THINK THERE IS
A PROGRAM INITIALLY PUT IN PLACE
IN TIJUANA ON THE BORDER OF
CALIFORNIA ESSENTIALLY FORCING
FAMILY UNITS TO WAIT OUT THEIR
ASYLUM CLAIMS ON THE MEMBERS KA
SIDE OF THE BORDER.
THERE IS SOME TALK OF EXPANDING
THAT PROGRAM ON VARIOUS POINTS
OF THE SOUTHERN BORDER.
THIS, THE CRITICS OF THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN WHAT
THEY SEE AS A DETRIMENTAL ISSUE
THAT WILL CONTINUE TO PUT THESE
FAMILIES AND THESE CHILDREN IN
HARM'S WAY.
YOU ARE ESSENTIALLY ASKING
PEOPLE COMING HERE AND ASKING
FOR A LEGAL PROCESS, REQUESTING
ASYLUM AND FORCING THEM TO WAIT
IN THESE COMMUNITIES ALONG THE
U.S.-SOUTHERN BORDER, WHERE THEY
ARE MUCH MORE, THERE IS MUCH
MORE DANGEROUS SITUATIONS BEING
TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF, THREATENED,
THAT SORT OF THING.
>> THAT IS THE CONCERN FOR A LOT
OF ORGANIZATIONS THAT ARE TRYING
TO HELP THESE MIGRANTS WHO ARE
ARRIVING HERE IN THESE BORDER
REGIONS.
>> CAN I JUST ASK YOU, MARY, ED,
IF EITHER OF YOU KNOW, THERE
HAVE BEEN REPORTS RECENTLY OF
TWO KIDS THAT DIED IN ONE OF
THESE CENTRES IN MEXICO.
IS IT FACTUALLY CORRECT HOW THAT
HAPPENED?
ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT THE
HAPPENING MORE?
>> IT IS FACTUALLY CORRECT.
WE KNOW THAT THREE CHILDREN WERE
KIDNAPPED IN TIJUANA.
THEY HAD BEEN STAYING AT A YOUTH
SHELTER BECAUSE THEY WERE NOT
ALLOWED TO APPLY FOR ASYLUM.
TWO WERE MERD D MURDERED.
ONE WAS ALLOWED TO ESCAPE AND
BRING BACK THE MESSAGE BASICALLY
THAT CHILDREN ARE IN DANGER AND
CHILDREN ARE IN DANGER.
FAMILIES ARE IN DANGER.
THERE IS A DANGEROUS WAY TO
CONDUCT A POLICY.
THIS MEANS THAT PEOPLE ARE
TRAPPED IN BORDER CITIES WHERE
USERS AND GOONGS AND THE FOLKS
THAT PEOPLE ARE FLEEING KNOW
PEOPLE ARE TRAPPED AND SO PEOPLE
ARE IN GRAVE DANGER.
PEOPLE HAVE DIED BECAUSE OF THE
POLICIES.
MORE PEOPLE WILL DIE UNLESS THIS
POLICY IS CHANGED.
WE KNOW THAT THAT IS ON OUR
HANDS.
>> ON THIS SIDE OF THE BORDER,
LET ME PLAY ANOTHER LITTLE CLIP
FROM COMMANDER, THE COMMANDER
WHO WE HEARD, JONATHAN WHITE
FROM HHS.
WE HEARD HIM IN THE LEAD-IN
TALKING ABOUT THE TRAWLER FOR
THE KIDS.
HE TALKED ABOUT THIS POLICY OF
HOUSING SEPARATED CHILDREN, HE
HAD TO ENFORCE IT.
HE NEVER WOULD HAVE ENFORCED
THIS POLICY HIMSELF.
JUST LISTEN TO THIS.
>> THE CONCERN WHICH I EXPRESSED
WERE TWO.
FIRST, THAT THIS WOULD BE
INCONSISTENT WITH OUR LEGAL
REQUIREMENT TO ACT IN THE BEST
INTEREST OF THE CHILD AND WOULD
EXPOSE CHILDREN TO UNNECESSARY
RISK OF HARM.
SECOND, THAT IT WOULD EXCEED THE
CAPACITY OF THE PROGRAM, ISSUES
OF THAT CAPACITY ARE VERY
IMPORTANT BECAUSE IT CONSTITUTES
OUR ABILITY TO PROVIDE A SAFE
AND APPROPRIATE ENVIRONMENT TO
EVERY CHILD.
>> WE'VE ONLY GOT FIRST TIME
SECONDS LEFT, ED LAVANDARA, IN
YOUR REPORTING, HAVE YOU HEARD
SIMILAR MISTAKES GIVINGS FROM
OFFICIALS WHO HAVE TO ENFORCE
SOME OF THIS POLICY?
>> Reporter: THAT TO ME THAT WAS
THE FIRST TIME I HAVE HEARD
PEOPLE IN AN OFFICIAL CAPACITY
SAY THAT THAT WAS MADE THAT
STATEMENT THERE IN THAT
CONGRESSIONAL SETTING SO
STRIKING.
>> WELL, MARY, DO YOU ALWAYS
FIND IT EXTRAORDINARY OR HAVE
YOU HEARD IT BEFORE?
>> NO, THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME I
HAVE HEARD THAT.
THAT IS THE CONGRESS AM
STATEMENT OF ATTEMPT THEY ARE
SUPPOSED TO BE ACTING IN THE
BEST ACTION OF CHILDREN.
WHAT WE SEE THAT HAS NOT BEEN
HANG, JUST THE OPPOSITE HAS BEEN
HAPPENING.
>> MARY BOWER, ED LAVANDARA,
THANK YOU FOR JOINING ME THIS
EVENING.
>>> NOW WE DIG INTO AMERICA'S
COMPLICATED RELATIONSHIP WITH
DATA AND UNDER SURVEILLANCE.
MICHAEL CHERTOFF WAS PRESIDENT
GEORGE W. BUSH'S HOMELAND
SECURITY SECRETARY.
BUT BEFORE THAT HE MADE A NAME
FOR HIMSELF CO-AUTHORING THE
U.S. PATRIOT ACT IN THE WAKE OF
THE 9/11 ATTACKS.
THE ACT MASSIVELY EXPANDED
GOVERNMENT UNDER SURVEILLANCE.
IT ALLOWED THE DETENTION OF
IMMIGRANTS, SOME THINK THE
SUPREME COURT STRUCK DOWN, NOW
CHERTOFF IS DISCUSSING THE
GROWING THREAT TO PRIVACY AS WE
HAT TOWN IS U DOWN WITH US AND
YES THEY TOUCHED ON THAT BORDER
WALL.
>>?
MICHAEL, LET'S START WITH THINGS
IN THE NEWS NOW AND ABSTRACT UP.
FIRST, IMMIGRATION.
YOU WERE THE SECOND HEAD OF
HOMELAND SECURITY AND SERVED
UNDER PRESIDENT BUSH.
HOW IMPORTANT IS A PHYSICAL
BARRIER THAT'S AT THE CENTER OF
ALL THIS?
>> IT'S A VERY SMALL PIECE OF
WHAT YOU WANT.
WHEN WE WERE IN OFFICE, I THINK
WE BUILT ABOUT 650 MILES OF
BARRIERS ALONG CERTAIN AREAS
WHERE YOU DISTANCE BETWEEN THE
BORDER AND SAY A MAJOR TONY OR A
HIGHWAY WAS VERY SHORT.
AND, THEREFORE, YOU WOULDN'T BE
ABLE TO INTERCEPT PEOPLE IF THEY
CROSSED THE BORDER.
YOU COULD PROBABLY BUILD ANOTHER
50 OR SO MILES AND FIND SOME
USEFUL PLACES FOR IT.
BUT IT'S ONLY A VERY SMALL PART
OF WHAT YOU WANT.
WHAT YOU REALLY NEED IS
TECHNOLOGY, BOARD PARE TROLL
PERSONNEL, A DETENTION
FACILITIES FOR PEOPLE WHO WILL
BE DEPORT AND IT HAS TO BE
INTEGRATED INTO A SYSTEM.
SO THE IDEA THAT YOU WANT A WALL
IS A MISTAKES CHARACTERIZATION
FOR WHAT THE REAL REQUIREMENT
IS.
>> IS IT WORTH SHUTTING THE
GOVERNMENT OVER?
>> IT'S NOT WORTH SHUTTING THE
GOVERNMENT OVER.
THE DISAPPOINTING THING IS IF
YOU ACTUALLY GOT THE
PROFESSIONALS TOEBLG, THEY COULD
MAP OUT PRETTY CLEARLY GIVEN
WHAT THEY KNOW EXACTLY WHERE YOU
WANT PHYSICAL BARRIERS, WHERE
YOU WANT TECHNOLOGY, WHERE YOU
WANT DRONES AND THAT WOULD BE
THE INTELLIGENT WAY TO SPEND THE
MONEY.
IRONICALLY, WHEN THERE IS
COMPLAINING ABOUT DRUGS COMING
THROUGH THE COUNTRY, THE VAST
MAJORITY OF THAT COMES THROUGH
THE PORTS OF ENTRY.
SO IF YOU HAD EQUIPMENT AT THE
PORTS OF ENTRY THAT WOULD ALLOW
YOU BETTER VISIBILITY TO WHAT IS
CONCEALED IN AN AUTOMOBILE AND
TRUCK, THAT WOULD DO MUCH MORE
TO REDUCE THE IMPLICATION OF
DRUGS AND BARRIERS IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE DESERT.
BARRIERS REALLY DISCOURAGE A
CERTAIN KIND OF CASUAL CROSSER.
IT DOESN'T DISCOURAGE SOMEONE
WHO IS INVESTING LARGE AMOUNTS
OF MONEY TO MOVE VERY VALUABLE
DRUGS AND THEY WANT VOLUME AND
THEY'RE GOING TO BASICALLY TRY
TO USE EXISTING TRANSPORTATION
SYSTEMS TO COME THROUGH PORTS OF
ENTRY.
>> EVEN IN A NATIONAL EMERGENCY?
>> I WOULDN'T SAY IT'S A
NATIONAL EMERGENCY.
OBVIOUSLY, BORDER PATROL IS AN
IMPORTANT FEDERAL OBJECTIVE.
ITEMLY THE RATE OF CROSSING
ALTHOUGH FLUCTUATING OVER TIME
HAS GENERALLY GONE DOWN.
WHAT'S REALLY DRIVING IT NOW IS
LARGELY CONDITIONS IN PARTS OF
CENTRAL AMERICA WHERE YOU HAVE,
NOT ONLY ECONOMIC ISSUES BUT
HAVE YOU GANG VIOLENCE, HAVE YOU
LACK OF RULE OF LAW AND PEOPLE
ARE FLEEING BECAUSE THEY'RE
AFRAID FOR THEIR LIVES THE BEST
WAY TO STOP THAT IS TO WORK WITH
THE CENTRAL AMERICAN GOVERNMENTS
TO REINSTITUTE THE RULE OF LAW
TO BUILD THE ECONOMY AND KEEP
THE WORLD HAPPY TO STAY IN THEIR
HOMES.
>> ANOTHER REASON, THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE LAID OUT
AN INDICTMENT AGAINST HAUWEI.
IF UNITED STATES HAS BEEN
PRESSURING OR LEVERAGE COUNTRIES
AROUND THE WORLD TO FOUGHT USE
EQUIPMENT FROM THIS TELECOM
COMPANY AS THE WORLD UPGRADES TO
35G.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT IT THAT'S
IMPORTANT?
>> THIS IS ACTUALLY NOT NEW.
THE ISSUE OF CHINESE TECHNOLOGY
HAS POTENTIALLY CREATING AN
OPPORTUNITY FOR THE CHINESE TO
EXIT ACTS OF ESPIONAGE OR ACTS
OF SABOTAGE HAS BEEN DISCUSSED
AMONG SECURITY PEOPLE FOR THE
LAST TEN YEARS OR SO WE SAW
EARLIER THIS YEAR AN INDICTMENT
OF HAUWEI FOR STEALING
TECHNOLOGICAL SECRETS FROM
T-MOBILE.
THAT'S HAPPENED IN THE PAST THAT
WILL CONTINUE TO HAPPEN.
BUT BEYOND THAT I THINK THERE IS
A CONCERN THAT YOU ARE
POTENTIALLY PUTTING THE NEXT
GENERATION OF CRITICAL
TECHNOLOGY IN THE HANDS OF A
COUNTRIES WHICH MAY BE AN
ADVERSARY IF CERTAIN RESPECTS.
WE'VE PUBLISHED A REPORT CALLED
FREEDOM ON THE NET AND IN THE
REPORT, WE DETAIL HOW THE
CHINESE ARE USING THE EXPLOITS
OF I.T. TECHNOLOGY TO EMBED
THEMSELVES AROUND THE WORLD IN
ASIA AND AFRICA AND THEY'RE
ACTUALLY TEACHING SOME OF THE
LOCAL GOVERNMENTS THERE HOW TO
USE TECHNOLOGY TO BETTER CONTROL
THE POPULOUS AND TO SUPPRESS
FREE SPEECH.
SO WE'RE IN A SITUATION NOW
WHERE IF YOU HAVE CHINESE
COMPANIES THAT ARE IN CRITICAL
NODES AROUND THE WORLD, ARE YOU
ESSENTIALLY, PROGRAMS, ENABLING
THE EXPORT AUTHORITARIANISM TO
PARTS OF THE WORLD THAT ARE
FREE.
>> HOW DO THE WEST COUNTER THAT?
IS FROM A WAY THAT YOU CAN GET
THE WORLD TO AGREE ON THE RULES
OF THE ROAD?
>> WELL, I DO THINK THERE ARE
THINGS THAT WE CAN DO, EASTERN
USING MULTI-STAKE HOLDER
APPROACH.
THEY'RE UNDER WAY RIGHT NOW.
FOR EXAMPLE, I THINK MANY OF THE
WESTERN COUNTRIES DO HAVE A MORE
OR LESS A COMMON SET OF VALUES
AND COULD REASONABLY REALLY
REACH AGREEMENTS ON SOME OF THE
THINGS WE ARE TALKING ABOUT AND
BECAUSE OF THE FACT THAT THESE
COUNTRIES ARE STILL
CORRECTIVELY, BY FAR, THE MOST
POWERFUL ECONOMIC ACTORS ON THE
GLOBE, IN THE END IF WE DO HAVE
A RESET OF VALUES AND AGREED
APPROACH, I THINK THAT CAN DRIVE
THE CHINESE TO ACCOMMODATE TO
THAT AS WELL.
AND I'M ON A GLOBAL COMMISSION
FOR STABILITY NOW WHICH HAS
DRAWN PEOPLE FOCUSING ON CYBER
ISSUES TO TRY TO COME UP WITH
SOME NORMS THAT CAN BE GLOBALLY
ACCEPTED TO HAVE AN OPEN
INTERNET, A FREE INTERNET AND AN
INTERNET THAT IS NOT FRAGMENTED
BUT RATHER IS TRULY GLOBAL IN
IT.
>> YOU WROTE A BOOK RECENTLY
TALKING ABOUT THE DATA EXPLOSION
AND HAVE YOU KIND OF A SIMPLE
IDEA IN DATA 1.0, 2.0, 3.0,
BREAK THAT DOWN FOR US?
>> I WROTE THE BOOK BECAUSE I
THOUGHT PEOPLE DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
THE MATTER IN WHICH DATA IS
BEING CHECKED AND HOW WE'RE
USING NEWS NOW AND HOW IT WILL
TRANSFORM THE WAY WE LIVE.
SO I LOOK BACK HISTORICALLY.
IF YOU LOOK AT MOST OF HUMAN
HISTORY, DATA WAS BASICALLY WHAT
YOU SAID WHAT YOU HEARD, WHAT
WAS WRITTEN DOWN, WHAT WAS
PUBLISHED AND WE WERE MAINLY
CONCERNED ABOUT PROTECTING OUR
PRIVACY IN THE SENSE OF OUR
PROPERTY.
IT WAS AN EXPRESSION HEARING.
EVERY MAN'S HOME IS HIS CASTLE.
IT GOES BACK A FEW HUNDRED YEARS
AND THE IDEA WAS YOUR PRIVACY IS
BACK TO YOUR PROPERTY.
NO ONE CAN ENTER THROUGH YOUR
HOUSE WITHOUT A WARRANT.
WHEN YOU GOT TO LESSEN, ALL OF A
SUDDEN PROPERTY WAS NOT THE
ISSUE ANYMORE.
IT WAS CONFIDENTIALITY.
COULD I KEEP MY CONVERSATIONS
PRIVATE?
COULD I KEEP MY IMAGE PRIVATE?
AND THEREFORE THE LAW STARTED TO
CHANGE, TO RECOGNIZE WE HAVE TO
FOCUS ON PROPERTY AND NOW WE
HAVE TO FOCUS CONFIDENTIALITY.
MY POINT NOW IS, GIVEN THE
AMOUNT OF DATA THAT IS BEING
GENERATED, NOT ONLY WHAT WE
VOLUNTARILY GENERATE BUT WHAT IS
GENERATED ABOUT US.
THE FACT THAT IT IS NOW STORED
INDEFINITELY.
IT CAN BE PUBLISHED ALL OVER THE
WORLD.
SHOULD WE TRY TO KEEP THINGS
HIDDEN OR SECRET?
THAT SHIP HAS SAILED.
NOW WE TALK ABOUT WHO CONTROLS
THE DATA?
WHAT IS YOUR RIGHT EVEN WHEN THE
DATA IS COLLECTED TO BE ABLE TO
SAY YES OR NO TO HOW IT'S BEING
USED?
>> THEY'RE ISSUING AUTONOMY.
>> EXACTLY.
IT'S ABOUT FREEDOM AND CHINA,
CHINA ARE WORKING ON A SOCIAL
CREDITOR, WHERE EVERYTHING THAT
YOU DO WILL BE COMPILED AND YOU
ESSENTIALLY GET A RATING AS TO
WHETHER YOU ARE A GOOD OR A BAD
THING.
IF YOU ARE GOOD, YOU GET
PREFERENCE AND ALL KIND OF
THINGS LIKE JOBS AND EDUCATION.
AND IF NOT, YOU COULD BE SHUT
OUT OF THINGS.
NOW IMAGINE THAT IN A WESTERN
SOCIETY, AND IT MIGHT BE
PRIVATE, WHERE YOUR ABILITY TO
GET A JOB OR GET INSURANCE OR
FIND A PLACE TO LIVE WOULD BE
AFFECTED BY WHETHER AN ALGORITHM
LOOKS AT EVERYTHING YOU DO,
THAT'S RECORDING IN SOME FORM OR
FAX OF DATA AND MAKES A JUDGMENT
OF WHETHER YOU ARE DESIRABLE OR
NOT A DESIRABLE PERSON.
>> ISN'T THAT STARTING TO HAPPEN
ALREADY?
IF A HEALTH INSURER HAD ACCESS
TO MY SHOPPING LIST, IT COULD
CHANGE MY RATES.
BEING REALLY HEALTHY AND MAYBE
EQUALS OUT PUT.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU HAVE A GYM
MEMBERSHIP LOCKING IN FIVE TIMES
A WEEK.
OKAY.
HE'S NOT GOING TO DIE, VERSUS A
BAG OF M AND AND Ms, NETFLIX
BINGEING.
>> BUT THAT'S HAPPENING NOW,
EVEN I PUBLISHED A BOOK ABOUT
SIX MONTHS AGO AND THERE ARE
MORE STORIES ABOUT INSURANCE
COMPANIES SAYING, WE WANT TO SEE
YOUR FitBit.
HOW MUCH EXERCISE ARE YOU
GETTING?
AND THEY'RE ALSO LOOKING AT
THINGS LIKE, EXACTLY WHAT FOODS
DO YOU EAT WHEN YOU GO TO A
RESTAURANT?
WHAT DO YOU EAT AT A RESTAURANT.
HOW WAS YOUR SLEEP PATTERN?
IMAGINE ALL OF THIS BEING
COLLECTED AND PRETTY SOON YOUR
FREEDOM TO DECIDE WHAT YOU WANT
TO DO WILL ALWAYS BE SUBJECT TO
A NAGGING FEAR THAT YOU ARE
GOING TO BE PUNISHED.
THERE WAS A BBC THAT WAS ON THAT
ACTUALLY TOOK THIS, I'D LIKE TO
SAY TO AN EXTREME, NOT THAT
EXTREME ABOUT A WORLD IN WHICH
LITERALLY EVERYBODY IS BEING
RAIDED UP AND DOWN MINUTE BY
MINUTE AND IT MAKES 1984,
GEORGERWELL'S DISTOPIAN NOVEL
LOOK LIKE A KINDER GAT INNER'S
DREAM THERE THIS IS THE GUY THAT
HELPED WRITE THE PATRIOT ACT.
AT THE TIME YOU WERE NOT IN THAT
DATA CLIMATE WE ARE IN TODAY.
THERE WASN'T AMAZON NEARLY AS
POWERFUL AND ALL KNOWING WHAT IT
IS.
WHAT IS THE BALANCE BETWEEN
GIVING THE GOVERNMENT THE
OPPORTUNITIES TO CHASE DOWN AND
GET AS MUCH INFORMATION, PREVENT
ATTACKS, ET CETERA?
AND THAT SENSE OF AUTONOMY THAT
YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT WHERE I
STILL FEEL LIKE I HAVE SOME
LEVEL OF CONTROL OVER WHAT I
CHOOSE TO SHARE WITH ESPECIALLY
THE BODY GOVERNING ME?
>> WELL, WE ARE RIGHT TO BE
CONCERNED ABOUT THE GOVERNMENT
AS WELL AS THE PRIVATE SECTOR.
WHAT IS INTERESTING IS THAT THE
GOVERNMENT OPERATES ON MUCH MORE
CONSTRAINTS THAN A PRIVATE
SECTOR.
THE GOVERNMENT DOESN'T EVEN
DREAM OF COLLECTING DIVINE
INFORMATION THAT'S COLLECTED IN
THE PRIME SECTOR AND BEFORE THE
GOVERNMENT USES IT, THERE ARE
ALL KIND OF DATES THEY HAVE TO
GO THROUGH, AT LEAST IN THE
UNITED STATES AND OTHER
COUNTRIES ARE ACTUALLY
DIFFERENT.
SO, FOR EXAMPLE, TO COLLECT
CONTENT OF INFORMATION E-MAILS
ARE BEING DISCUSSED OVER THE
TELEPHONE, EITHER ONE.
NOW THERE IS A MOVEMENT I THINK
FOR CORRECTLY TO REQUIRE A
WARRANT, EVEN FOR OLDER, NOT
JUST CURRENT E-MAILS, TO USE THE
INFORMATION, YOU HAVE TO GO
THROUGH VARIOUS KIND OF HOOPS TO
GET PERMISSION.
SO I DO THINK THAT THE
GOVERNMENT, ALTHOUGH YOU CAN
ALWAYS ARGUE ABOUT WHAT THEY
OUGHT TO DO, IT DOES OPERATE
UNDER A REGIME WHERE THEY ARE
CONTROLLED.
>> THERE HAVE BEEN SO MANY
EXAMPLES WHERE EVEN IF THOSE
PERMISSION SYSTEMS HAVE EXISTED,
THERE HAS BEEN SUCH A LACK OF
TRANSPARENCY THAT IT SHAKES OUR
FOUNDATIONAL TRUST IN THE
GOVERNMENT SAYING, HEY, IF THE
NSA HAS THIS PROGRAM, WHETHER
THEY WERE AUTHORIZED OR NOT, IT
SEEMS SHADY, IT'S ONE MORE THING
I HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT.
>> I AGREE WITH YOU, I THINK
TRANSPARENTSCY WILL BE
IMPORTANT.
ONE OF THE MISTAKES TAKES THE
GOVERNMENT MADE OVER A PERIOD OF
TIME, FOR EXAMPLE THE COURT OF
OPINION OF THE KOIRT THAT
SUPERVISORS UNDER SURVEILLANCE
IT'S KEPT CLASSIFIED.
AFTER SNOWDEN YOU KNOW DID HIS
RELEASE OF CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION, THE GOVERNMENT
STARTED TO DECLASSIFY THE
OPINIONS.
I THINK WHAT WAS PUT OUT, A, WAS
FOUGHT PARTICULARLY DAMAGING TO
NATIONAL SECURITY.
BUT FOR THE FIRST TIME PEOPLE
COULD SEE, WOW THE JUDGES ARE
REALLY DIGGING INTO THIS.
THEY COULD SEE THE REASONING OF
THE COURT AND, FRANKLY, I THINK
THE GOVERNMENT WOULD HAVE BEEN
BETTER SERVED HAD THEY PUT THIS
OUT BEFORE ANY OF THIS BUSINESS
HAPPENED.
I AGREE, I THINK A LESSON FOR
THE GOVERNMENT THE YOU HAVE TO
ASK YOURSELF IS THIS SECRECY
REALLY NECESSARY OR WILL WE
ACTUALLY GET MORE VALUE BY AT
LEAST IN A GENERALIZED WAY,
MAKING PUBLIC WHAT WE'RE DOING
TO WHAT THE RULES ARE.
>> A CORE QUESTION HERE IS THE
4th AMENDMENT.
RIGHT?
WHAT IS UNREASONABLE SEARCH AND
CEASE E SEIZURE IN THIS NEW ERA
THAT WE ARE GOING INTO?
IS MY HEART RATE INFORMATION AND
MY SLEEP HABITS, SITTING IN THE
SERVERS OF THE THIRD PARTY.
DO I HAVE CONTROL OF THAT
INFORMATION AND WHO SHOULD BE
ABLE TO TRANSACT THAT?
>> I WOULD GUESS EXACTLY THE
ISSUE WE ARE FACING.
HOW WE ARE CREATING SO MUCH
DIFFERENT DATA, WE HAVE TO
UNDERSTAND WHO GOVERNS IT.
WHAT ARE THE RULES THAT APPLY TO
THE ISSUE OF ACCESS AND THAT'S
ALREADY BEGINNING TO CHANGE.
I'LL GIVE YOU AN EXAMPLE.
YEARS AGO, MANY YEARS AGO,
ADOPTING BORDER SEARCHES, WE
WERE PROMULGATED BY THE SUPREME
COURT.
WHICH CROSS THE BORDER TO COME
INTO THE U.S., BORDER OFFICIALS
ARE ABLE SEARCH ANYTHING YOU
CARRY WITH YOU.
YOU HAVE A LIMIT TO WHAT YOU CAN
PURCHASE REPORT INTO THE U.S.
THAT WAS APPLIED TO LAPTOPS AND
OTHER REPOSITORY DATA, BECAUSE
YOU ARE BRINGING IT INTO THE
UNDERSTAND K. NOW VERY RECENTLY
THE ISSUE WAS RAISED WHAT DO YOU
DO, FOR EXAMPLE, THE SMART HOME
WHICH IS CONNECTED TO THE CLOUD.
SO IF YOU ARE ABLE OPEN UP THE
PHONE AND SEARCH THE PHONE, YOU
ARET NOT ONLY GETTING ON THE
PHONE, ARE GETTING WHAT MAY BE
SITTING ON AMAZON SERVERS
SOMEWHERE IN THE UNITED STATES.
IT WOULD BE AS IF I SEARCHED YOU
WHEN YOU CAME INTO COUNTRY.
AND THE SUPREME COURT CAN
ACCOUNT FOR THE SHEER VOLUME OF
MATERIAL THAT IS NOW AVAILABLE
ON A PHONE OR A LOOPTOP.
>> I WANT TO ASK ALSO ABOUT
UPCOMING ELECTIONS, ARE THERE IS
TWO LEVELS.
ARE STATE SYSTEMS IN THE UNITED
STATES SECURE ENOUGH?
>> TWO LEVELS, THE
INFRASTRUCTURE, THAT IS THE
VOTING MACHINES AN VOTER
REGISTRATION ROLLS AND
TABULATION.
I THINK IT'S VERY UNEASY,
CONGRESS IS TRYING TO GET MORE
MONEY, THE DEPARTMENT OF
HOMELAND SECURITY IS WORKING
WITH SOME OF THE STATES THAT
UPGRADE THEIR SECURITY OF THE
INFRASTRUCTURE.
AND THERE ARE SOME THINGS THAT I
HAVE BEEN INVOLVED IN THE
COMMISSION ON ELECTION INTEGRITY
WHERE WE ARE TRYING TO PROMOTE
THAT.
THE LARGER ISSUE, THOUGH, IS
WHAT THEY CALL INFORMATION
OPERATIONS.
IT'S THE USE BY FOREIGN
GOVERNMENTS, LIKE THE RUSSIANS
OR EVEN FRANKLY BY PEOPLE IN OUR
OWN COUNTRY OF TOOLS DESIGNED TO
MANIPULATE PUBLIC OPINION AND
CREATE THERE UNITY AND EVEN
SUPPRESS VOTING BY PROPAGATING
STORIES OR MAGNIIFYING
DISTURBING STORIES, ALL TO PLAY
WITH EMOTIONS.
THERE ARE SOME THINGS YOU CAN DO
TO MITIGATE THAT, PARTICULARLY
WHEN HAVE YOU FOREIGN GOVERNMENT
INVOLVED.
BUT AGAIN, SOME OF THIS IS GOING
TO REQUIRE THE HARD WORK AND THE
EDUCATION OF THE PEOPLE ABOUT
HOW TO BE CRITICAL THINKERS.
THIS IS ABOUT TO GET MORE
CHALLENGING, BECAUSE WE ARE NOW
ON THE VERGE OF WHAT THEY CALL
FAKES.
WHICH IS THE ABILITY TO CREATE
AUDIO AND VIDEO THAT IS
COMPLETELY FABRICATED THAT MAKES
IT SEEM LIKE A REAL PERSON IS
SAYING SMCHLTH AND IF THAT
STARTS TO GET USED AGAINST
CANDIDATES, FOR EXAMPLE, WILL
YOU REALLY HAVE STRESS ON THE
NOTION OF DETERMINING WHAT THE
TRUTH IS.
>> WHAT HAPPENS TO OUR
PROFESSION?
>> WELL, A BIG PIECE OF THIS IS
ACTUALLY BEING PUT ON
JOURNALISM.
HOW DO YOU MEASURE AND DETEBT
WHETHER SOMETHING IS PALS?
HOW DO YOU MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
GET CAUGHT UP IN THE --
>> ON THE COMPETITION FOR AGAIN
ZSA?
>> THE COMPETITION FOR CLIFFS
WHICH DRIVES THE BEHAVIOR YOU
ARE TRYING TO FIGHT AGAINST.
REINJECTING AN ELEMENT OF
PROFESSIONALISM AND JUDGMENT IN
THE WAY EDITORIAL DECISIONS ARE
MADE.
I THINK THERE IS AN IMPORTANT
PART OF PRESERVING OUR
DEMOCRACY.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> A DIFFICULT CHALLENGE AHEAD.
BEFORE WE GO, REMEMBER TO TUNE
IN TOMORROW WHEN WE WILL HAVE A
SPECIAL PROGRAM ON HUMANITY'S
BIGGEST TRIAL, THAT IS CLIMATE
CHANGE.
I WILL SPEAK WITH THE WASHINGTON
GOVERNOR, MAKING IT THE CENTER
OF A POSSIBLE PRESIDENTIAL
CAMPAIGN AND I'LL TALK TO THE
FLAFR GAMES BALOG, WHO HAS
DEVOTED HIS LIFE, HE HAS A NEW
FILM TO HUMAN ELEMENTS.
THANK YOU U THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AMANPOUR AND COMPANY ON
PBS AND JOIN US AGAIN NEXT TIME.
♪♪
-PNC Bank values the importance
of pubpr
♪♪
NARRATOR:
Funding for "American Masters"
is provided by...
the Corporation
for Public Broadcasting...
Support for this program
also provided by
the National Endowment
for the Arts.
Art works.
The Paul W. Zuccaire Foundation,
and by contributions to your PBS
station from viewers like you.
Thank you.
-You know, just gather around
quietly. Come on.
Now, just stand by.
Here he is now.
Say, Fats, a bunch of the kids
would like to listen
to you blowin' up a storm.
Would you let them listen in?
-Well, as a rule
we don't do it.
But for the kids,
I'm more than glad.
-Hooray.
-♪ I like the way you walk ♪
♪ I like to
hear you talk ♪
♪ Let me hold your hand ♪
♪ And try to understand ♪
♪ I want a girl like you ♪
♪ Tell my trouble to ♪
♪ Don't be afraid ♪
♪ You've heard what I said ♪
MAN: Fats,
how'd this rock 'n' roll
all get started, anyway?
-Well, what they call
rock 'n' roll
now is rhythm and blues.
I've been playin'
for 15 years in New Orleans.
♪ I love you the best ♪
♪ Let the four winds blow ♪
-NARRATOR: A native son
of New Orleans, Fats Domino
would pioneer the big beat sound
and become one of the world's
most beloved entertainers.
[Instrumental]
Antoine Domino, Jr.,
arrived on February 26, 1928,
delivered by a midwife
with the assistance
of his grandmother, Carmelite,
who had been born into slavery.
Antoine Jr. was the last
of eight Domino children
and the only one to be born
in New Orleans.
-MAN: The -- the neighborhood
that Fats Domino grew up in
is called the Lower Ninth Ward
in New Orleans.
And it's arguably where a lot
of the best musicians came from.
And it's a part of the city
that enjoys a reputation
in New Orleans for being...
That's the -- the heart, really,
the heartbeat of the city.
-MAN: It was almost
like another, uh,
world, like another world.
There was always talk about...
When you talked
about the Lower Ninth Ward,
you talk as if the people
who lived down there
didn't have as much goin' on
as the people mid-city.
Of course, some of the people
who lived down there had a lot
goin' on.
-DOMINO: I was born
on Jourdan Avenue down here
in the Ninth Ward.
They said I was born in a house
at 1939 Jourdan Avenue.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I went to a school
right down the street here.
It was about 10 blocks
from here, McCartey School.
And then I remember years
ago when I used --
used to come home from school.
My mom used to be cooking, um,
on a wood stove.
And sometimes I
got from school, uh,
and I had to cut wood
that evening.
Another thing I remember
when I lived on Jourdan Avenue,
I used to pick iron and copper
in the street, Jourdan Avenue,
I used to live on.
The street was so bad,
the holes were so big
they used to get stuff
from the cotton bale and --
and and fill the street up
with nothin' but tin and iron.
That -- that's the way
Jourdan Avenue was.
And I used to sell it
to -- sell the scrap.
If you made your 20 cents
or 25 cents livin'...
That was a lot of money,
25 cents, in that time.
-When he got out
and about, he was,
uh, roamin' the streets
of the Ninth Ward.
And he would love to pick up
things that he'd see.
And sometimes he'd sell 'em
to the junkman who,
uh, ironically,
would become part
of the song "The Junker's Blues"
that he'd later record.
His life was changed, basically,
when his sister
married Harrison Verrett,
who was a, uh, relatively
well-known New Orleans musician
who played banjo.
♪♪
-DOMINO: My brother-in-law
Harrison used to play
with Papa Celestin Band.
You know, and, uh, one time
I went to the French Quarter,
and I heard them play out
there several times.
That's where I really learned
from my brother-in-law,
Harrison Verrett.
He had a lot of patience.
He would take...
He -- he just loved bein'
with children, you know?
And that's
what I loved about him.
-COLEMAN: Fats had always played
around on the family piano
since they had bought it.
First of all,
they put it out in the garage
to keep him from, uh,
drivin' them crazy a little bit.
But he even quit school
because he wanted
to play the piano so much.
And, uh, so he only went
to the fourth grade.
Harrison actually taught him
how to play it.
And he put the notes
on the piano on pieces of tape.
And it was a beat-up piano.
You could actually see the metal
through the -- the ivory.
But, uh, Fats, you know,
got some sound out of it.
-DOMINO: We had an upright piano
in the house.
He'd teach me the chords,
the foundation.
If you know
how to play the chord,
he'd write the chord
down to you.
And you play this famous song,
playin' in the band,
just by the chord.
And after I learnt that, that's
when I just went on my own.
Everybody had a piano.
I used to stop.
And the -- the manager said,
"Where's Fats at?"
His son would say...
His son was Willie.
Willie'd say, "I don't know."
Say, "Well,
you got a piano over there.
You better go look. He might be
where you left the piano.
Where the piano at,
where Fats at."
-COLEMAN: From the late
'30s to the '40s,
Fats started listening
more to jukeboxes.
That's basically the way that
blacks heard music in those days
because not a lot of 'em
had record players.
There was no radio that
played black music at that time.
[Upbeat music playing]
Fats' primary love for music
was in the boogie-woogie
piano players.
He always listened to
Meade Lux Lewis
and Pete Johnson,
the great piano players.
His cousins had a, uh, bar.
And he actually not only
had a jukebox there,
he also had a sounding machine,
which was I guess kind
of a luxury in those days.
The one
he particularly remembered,
I think it was a video
called Low Down Dog.
It was actually a comedian
who was found his woman
foolin' around with different
guy in the kitchen, okay,
and somethin' like that.
And he -- he chased her.
And he -- he started
singin' this song,
pointin' his finger
at her sayin',
"I ain't gonna be your
low-down dog no more."
-♪ I ain't gonna be your
low-down dog no more ♪
♪ Ain't gonna be
your low-down dog no more ♪
-COLEMAN: People that knew it
at the time was Joe Turner
who was singin'.
He was just mimin' the song.
And was Pete Johnson who was
playin' the boogie-woogie piano.
-♪ Work all day,
don't you know, my babe ♪
-Fats loved that video.
And he actually started playing
"Low Down Dog."
And he kept playin' it
for the next half a century.
♪♪
-♪ Ooh wee ♪
♪ Oo-ooh wee ♪
♪ It's a low down shame... ♪
CLEARY: It's very hard
to find out
what his formative
influences are.
Basic blues,
old-style blues piano.
It's -- and it's --
And boogie-woogie, I mean, that,
you know, that --
Straight-up boogie-woogie.
-♪ Bad, bad whiskey ♪
♪ Bad, bad whiskey ♪
♪ Bad, bad whiskey
made me lose my happy home ♪
-COLEMAN: Another favorite
performer of Fats'
was Amos Milburn, who was
a great boogie-woogie player.
Amos played these
low-down blues.
And they were all really sexy.
Fats played blues
like Amos Milburn.
Another influence of Fats'
was Louis Jordan,
who was the most popular
black singer-performer
of the 1940s.
And he was famous
for all of his novelty songs.
But more significantly,
he did some songs
that I would almost consider
rockers, like "Caldonia."
♪♪
-♪ Walkin' with my baby ♪
♪ She got great, big feet ♪
♪ She's long, lean and lanky ♪
♪ And ain't had
nothin' to eat ♪
♪ But she's my baby ♪
♪ And I love her just the same ♪
♪ Crazy about that woman ♪
♪ 'Cause Caldonia is her name ♪
-COLEMAN: He's shouting.
And he's -- and he's playing
this heavy boogie-woogie beat.
And so that was a song that
almost everybody in New Orleans
played at one time or another.
-♪ I've always loved you, baby ♪
♪ 'Cause Caldonia is your name ♪
-COLEMAN: After Fats
started playing in the little
Ninth Ward clubs,
he started running
into different people
who would be influential
in his career.
The first one was probably
Billy Diamond,
who was a local band leader.
He was a bass player.
He was a little short go-getter.
Fats told me during those days,
Billy Diamond was the only
person who could find a gig.
Uh, he could find a gig
when nobody else could.
-I gave him
the name Fats before then,
before he even had a record.
I gave him the name Fats
after a guy named Fat Waller
back in them days.
He was a great piano player.
He got mad when I played piano,
called him fat.
"Don't call me fat.
Don't call me fat, brown boy.
I don't know
what you callin' me fat for.
I don't call you Fat Billy."
-NARRATOR: While Fats
was pounding out boogie-woogie
with Billy Diamond's Band
at the Hideaway
and other neighborhood clubs,
a New Orleans trumpet sensation
by the name of Dave Bartholomew
was on a roll.
-COLEMAN: Dave Bartholomew
was one of the most popular,
if not the most popular,
band leader in the city.
And occasionally Fats went
and see him and check him out.
Earl Palmer, who was, uh,
Dave's great drummer,
had him sit in one time.
Fats got up there
and played that little jam
and boogie-woogie,
"Swanee River Boogie,"
or whatever it was,
and maybe another song or two.
Dave Bartholomew
did not like that.
As a matter of fact,
he came up to Earl Palmer
and said afterwards,
"I thought I told you
not to let that guy sit in."
Of course, he had no clue
that they would have
a incredible history to come,
as far as making some
of the most influential records
in the next 10 or 15 years.
-NARRATOR: One night,
Bartholomew brought a man
from Imperial Records,
a Mr. Lew Chudd,
to see Fats perform
at a local club.
-DOMINO: I work at the Hideaway.
I was real famous
at the Hideaway for just playin'
other people number.
Dave and Lew Chudd
came down there one night.
Lew Chudd wanted to hear
me sing and play.
So I did.
-COLEMAN: Fats played
"The Junker's Blues."
-♪ They call,
they call me a junker ♪
-COLEMAN: Champion Jack Dupree
was the barrelhouse piano player
from New Orleans who recorded
the original version
of "The Junker Blues" in 1940
and had a, you know,
mild success with it.
And that was a song that really
sold Fats to Lew Chudd.
Lew said, "You know,
I gotta have this guy."
And he actually signed him
right there on the spot
that very night.
-DOMINO: And about a week later,
say about 2 weeks later,
we had got together
to record the first record,
"Fat Man," 1949.
-And we never looked back
for 25 years.
[Upbeat piano]
-Dave said, "We gonna record
'The Fat Man.'"
I said, "We are?"
Oh, I got excited.
Durin' that period of time,
we had a radio program,
"The Fat Man."
So when we got in the studio,
Dave said, "This is Fats,
The Fat Man."
I look at Dave, said, "Dave,
The Fat Man is a white man."
-♪ They call,
they call me The Fat Man ♪
♪ 'Cause I weigh 200 pounds ♪
♪ All the girls, they love me ♪
♪ 'Cause I know my way around ♪
♪ I was standin' ♪
♪ I was standin' on the corner ♪
♪ Of Rampart and Canal ♪
♪ I was watchin', watchin' ♪
♪ Watchin' all the Creole gals ♪
[Vocalizing]
-"Fat Man," the first hit
that he -- hit that he had,
the first record in 1949, was
basically "The Junker's Blues."
And he told me
this the other day.
He said, I asked him
about "The Fat Man. "
He said, "It's just
The Junker's Blues.
I just changed it to...
From 'they call me a junker,'
to --
to, 'they call me The Fat Man'."
♪♪
-Fats played it
as if it was his own.
It was very final
when Fats played.
If you had never heard
whoever played the original,
if you heard Fats Domino's
version, that was enough.
You can just take it from there.
♪♪
-So I would say,
"What we gonna call him?"
I said, "Hell,
we gonna call him Fat Man."
♪♪
As soon as they heard it,
that was it.
♪♪
♪ I'm goin', I'm goin',
goin' away ♪
♪ And then I'm
goin', goin' to stay ♪
♪ 'Cause women and a bad life ♪
♪ They're carryin'
this soul away ♪
-NARRATOR: With "The Fat Man"
rising to number one
in the February 1950 rhythm
and blues charts,
Lew Chudd's hunch had paid off.
He quickly reassembled Fats
with Dave Bartholomew and band
for additional sessions
at Cosimo Matassa's
Rampart Street studio.
Cosimo's J&M Music Shop was the
only recording studio in town
and was quickly becoming
the Mecca for record men
looking to cash in on
the New Orleans
rhythm and blues sound.
And Dave Bartholomew's little
orchestra became the house band
backing nearly every performance
recorded there.
-New Orleans produces a
disproportionately large amount
of talented musicians.
And it really comes up
with the raw material.
-MAN: It's the only place
in the world
where everybody,
even white listeners,
clap on two and four instead
of one and three.
Right away, you can tell if
a white dude's from New Orleans,
man, when you hear him clap.
He's on the beat.
And that's --
that's kind of, uh,
a -- a natural thing
with New Orleans people.
You got kids in the street,
man... It's a lot of talent,
musically,
if you stand on a certain way.
Well, look at the history
of the town.
There's always been music.
That's maybe why you're born
with a lot of it
instilled in you.
-You can call it the big beat,
the sweet beat whatever it is.
But New Orleans got the beat.
-There have always been
gigs in New Orleans.
There's only really
a few periods in the history
of New Orleans
in the 20th century where
there's been a really thriving
recording scene.
And, um, the fact
that there was is largely due
to Dave Bartholomew
and Cosimo Matassa.
♪♪
-TOUSSAINT: Cosimo Matassa
and Dave Bartholomew
put New Orleans on the map.
-The room was 15-by-16.
I started recording direct
to disk, which,
uh, had a couple
of good features about it.
For one thing,
you didn't do any editing.
You didn't do any pickups.
You didn't do any overdubbing.
You played the damn thing
from beginning to end.
And -- and that made
for performance.
And I think that helped me.
I started on the fact that
everybody performed together
beginning to end.
Had to be right.
I always, 'til today,
thought that my job
was to put on disk
what was happening out
in the studio.
It was OJT, as Dave told me --
"on the job training."
-Imperial wanted us to go
on a tour
after Fats' first record,
which was "Fat Man Blues."
The other side
was "Detroit City Blues."
We had 3 days...
It was late startin'
this tour 'cause
Fats would hide every time
we go to look for him 'cause
he was afraid to go on the tour.
He was, you know, shook up.
First time
he'd ever went on any tour.
And we -- we got to go on --
go with us on the trip
was Professor Longhair.
-I got nothin'
but stars with me:
Lee Allen, Professor Longhair,
Fat Domino, Dave Bartholomew,
Bob Foreman, Frank Fields.
We're playin' in a dump.
At 11:30, 12:00,
I said, "Wasn't he supposed to
pay me at intermission?"
Earl Palmer say, "I seen
that man go out the door."
I said, "Well, he goin' home
to get the money."
That been 40 years.
He ain't come back yet.
[Laughs]
♪♪
[Whistling]
-NARRATOR:
Between 1950 and 1955,
Fats recorded a steady stream
of singles for Imperial
with many of them charting high
in the R&B charts.
Things were buzzing
at Cosimo's studio.
And Dave Bartholomew
was the go-to guy
for all the record labels
wishing to record
in New Orleans.
♪ Well, I'm goin' to
New Orleans ♪
♪ I'm goin' to see
the Mardi Gras ♪
♪ Well, I'm goin' to
New Orleans ♪
♪ I'm goin' to see
the Mardi Gras ♪
♪ When I get to New Orleans ♪
♪ I want to know
what's carnival for ♪
[Whistling]
-NARRATOR:
He produced the sessions,
wrote the arrangements,
and used his band
to back the performers.
-He was the man number one.
He was the boss
with the hot sauce.
MATASSA: We didn't call
him The Chief for nothin'.
He was the chief.
He kept us focused,
and particularly people
like Fats he kept focused
because Fats tended to doodle
and ramble and -- and --
and that sort of thing.
I think, uh,
without a Dave,
there might not have been a Fats
in the national sense of it.
[Cheering and applause]
-DOMINO: Thank you.
-COLEMAN: Fats showed up in
his Cadillac at Cosimo's studio.
And Dave was cutting a session
with Lloyd Price.
And the piano player at the time
in Dave's band --
I think it was
Salvador Doucette --
was not really
cutting the triplets too well.
And so Fats was the perfect
answer to that problem.
And he asked Fats
if he would sit in.
And then he
played that amazing introduction
to "Lawdy Miss Clawdy."
♪♪
And then the triplets
and then a -- a solo
in the middle.
And it... "Lawdy Miss Clawdy"
became the biggest hit
of the year and knocked his own
number one, "Goin' Home,"
out of the charts.
[Playing]
-I think I played on that one.
-MAN: Yeah, you did.
-MAN: Yeah.
-Yeah. You did.
-MAN: And here it is,
"Alan Freed's
Rock 'n' Roll Party."
And here he is in person:
Alan Freed.
[Cheers and applause]
-Hello, everybody.
How are y'all?
Welcome to our rock 'n' roll
jubilee of stars.
And here we go to rockin'
with wailin' tenorman,
Freddy Mitchell
and the rock 'n' roll boogie!
Here we go.
-COLEMAN: Alan Freed had
actually started using
the phrase "rock 'n' roll"
at the end of 1954.
And the first ever so-called
rock 'n' roll concert
was his show in New York,
January of '55.
And it was an all-black show.
Alan Freed was using
the phrase rock 'n' roll
to popularize rhythm and blues
primarily with white teenagers.
-♪ Oh well good-bye ♪
♪ Although I'll cry ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
♪ You're the one to blame ♪
-COLEMAN: And so this --
this crossing point
was very significant
because Fats Domino came along
with his biggest hit ever.
And, of course,
that was "Ain't That a Shame."
-♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
♪ You're the one to blame ♪
♪ You broke my heart ♪
♪ When you said we'll part ♪
-That's nothing.
That was one sentence.
"Ain't That a Shame," it don't
have no bridge to it, no middle.
It's the same, uh, sentence
over and over again.
But we sold it with --
with the music.
Duh-duh, duh-dum, boom.
In other words, I had the whole
band playin' like a bass.
Boom, boom.
-♪ Me cry ♪
♪ When you said goodbye ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
-COLEMAN: It was also one
of his simplest songs ever.
If you listen to "Ain't
That a Shame," you'll see,
"You made me cry
when you said goodbye."
And that's actually
a classic Fats Domino lyric
because he --
he just wrote things in the most
simple terms possible.
-DOMINO: I remember them tellin'
me, "Your record goin' pop."
I didn't know
what he was talkin' about.
Lew Chudd,
see, "The record goin' pop.
You got a big record."
Well, I'm like...
We had sellers before.
"Goin' Home," "The Fat Man,"
you know --
that's what broke me through
everybody buyin' my record,
black and the white.
He say,
"You got a big one now."
♪ Tears fell like rain ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
-NARRATOR: The surprise success
of "Ain't That a Shame"
was a game-changer for both Fats
and Imperial Records.
Though finally achieving
a crossover hit
that was selling phenomenally to
both black and white audiences,
Dave and Fats could not have
predicted what would happen
within a week of its release.
♪♪
♪ You make me cry ♪
♪ When you said goodbye ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
-DOMINO: Mine was not a week.
Somebody told me, you know,
a fellow by the name
of Pat Boone
comin' out with your record
next week.
Hollerin' somethin' crazy.
-And Pat Boone
was a very, um, innocent,
white crooner, should we say.
And, uh, he just was kind of,
uh, you know,
tryin' to croon a song
that should have been a rocker.
-Keep in mind,
it was him, you know.
A lot of people wasn't gonna
buy us at all because we
were black, at that time.
You know, there was segregation
in music too.
I know that, you know,
"I don't wanna hear it."
But after they heard it a while,
it started growin' on you,
and that's it,
like anything else.
-DOMINO: He did it all right.
It sold a lot of records.
-NARRATOR: While
"Ain't That a Shame"
was burning up the 1955
R&B and pop charts,
other black artists
such as Chuck Berry
and Little Richard
were following Fats' lead.
-♪ Woo, hoo, hoo, hoo baby ♪
♪ Havin' me some fun tonight ♪
-NARRATOR: The rock 'n' roll era
had begun.
-MAN: Rolling master A.
Master A, take one.
♪♪
[Applause]
-NARRATOR: By early 1956,
Elvis Presley was the king
of the pop charts.
-♪ You know I can be found ♪
♪ Sitting home all alone ♪
-NARRATOR: Rockers Bill Haley
and the Comets,
Gene Vincent,
and Carl Perkins
were also grabbing the attention
of the nation's youth.
By March of 1956,
Fats' "I'm in Love Again"
became his second
top-10 hit.
Dave Bartholomew's big beat
was making Antoine Domino
a very famous man.
-♪ Yes, it's me,
and I'm in love again ♪
♪ Had no lovin'
since you know when ♪
♪ You know I love you,
yes I do ♪
♪ And I'm savin' all my lovin'
just for you ♪
♪ I need your lovin',
and I need it bad ♪
♪ Just like a dog
when he's goin' mad ♪
♪ Whoa-wee, baby, whoa-wee ♪
♪ Baby, won't you give your love
to me ♪
♪ Eeny-meeny and miney-mo ♪
♪ Told me you didn't want me
around no more ♪
♪ Whoa-wee, baby, whoa-wee ♪
♪ Baby, don't you let
your dog bite me ♪
[Instrumental]
♪ Yes, it's me,
and I'm in love again ♪
♪ Had no lovin'
since you know when ♪
♪ You know I love you,
yes I do ♪
♪ And I'm savin' all my lovin'
just for you ♪
♪ Eeny-meeny and miney-mo ♪
♪ Told me you didn't want me
around no more ♪
♪ Whoa-wee, baby, whoa-wee ♪
♪ Baby, don't you let
your dog bite me ♪
[Instrumental ending]
-NARRATOR: The year 1956
belonged to Fats Domino.
With nine records scoring
in the top-10
pop and rhythm and blues charts,
there was no stopping him.
And in that year,
he recorded the song for which
he will be forever remembered.
-♪ I found my thrill ♪
♪ On Blueberry Hill ♪
-COLEMAN: "Blueberry Hill"
was a pop standard
that had originally been
recorded in 1940
by Gene Autry
for a singin' cowboy movie.
But the most significant version
for Fats
was the Louis Armstrong version.
It was a phenomenal time
for him.
The unfortunate thing is that
Lew Chudd of Imperial Records
actually tried too hard to sell
Fats Domino to a white audience.
He thought that if you made
it sound more pop,
it would sell more white.
But he kind of missed the point
of Fats Domino.
And so he was having him record
all these standards.
Some worked, some didn't.
As "Blueberry Hill" proved,
when Fats redid
a standard,
he changed it all around
so the people
that knew the old standard,
they barely recognized it.
-And the rest is history.
A record that has,
I've been told,
sold over 5 1/2 million records,
"Blueberry Hill."
And of course,
his number one record
of all time.
♪ I found my thrill ♪
♪ On Blueberry Hill ♪
♪ When I found you ♪
♪ The moon stood still ♪
♪ On Blueberry Hill ♪
♪ And lingered until ♪
♪ My dream came... ♪
♪ The wind in the willow
played ♪
♪ Love's sweet melody ♪
♪ But all of the vows we made ♪
♪ Were never to be ♪
♪ Though we're apart ♪
♪ You're part of me still ♪
♪ For you were my thrill ♪
♪ On Blueberry Hill ♪
♪ The wind in the willow
played ♪
♪ Love's sweet melody ♪
♪ But all of the vows we made ♪
♪ Were never to be ♪
♪ Though we're apart ♪
♪ You're part of me still ♪
♪ For you were my thrill ♪
♪ On Blueberry Hill ♪
-COLEMAN: He had an amazing
string of success at that time.
But with "Blueberry Hill,"
"Blue Monday"
and "I'm Walkin',"
Fats had three huge hits
at the time.
Even Time magazine
recognized it.
He was huge.
He -- he was actually
headlining the biggest shows
in rock 'n' roll at that time.
People like Chuck Berry,
Little Richard, Buddy Holly,
the Everly Brothers
and Jerry Lee Lewis
were all underneath Fats.
They did not even approach
his record sales at that time.
He was selling a million records
every month.
-RAY: There was a time
he and Elvis Presley,
for a year or two there,
were neck and neck in sales.
People don't realize this.
-♪ I'm beat to my socks ♪
♪ My gal calls,
got to tell her that I'm out ♪
♪ 'Cause Thursday
is a hard workin' day ♪
♪ And Friday I get my pay ♪
-HARDESTY:
We did it in California.
And --
and recordin' "Blue Monday,"
they had another saxophone
player playin' the baritone.
He... Fats didn't like the way
he soloed on it.
He said, "Herbert, I
want you to play the baritone."
You want me
to play the baritone?
I got my tenor here.
He said, "No, please,
play the solo on baritone."
So I played the solo
on baritone.
And he went wild.
And the, uh, people love it,
like the da, da, da-da.
Let me see if I can play it
on my saxophone.
I don't have my strap.
[Playing]
♪♪
-"Blue Monday,"
I think that's one
of the greatest things
I ever wrote.
♪♪
-♪ Saturday mornin',
oh Saturday mornin' ♪
♪ All my tiredness
has gone away ♪
♪ Got my money and my honey ♪
♪ And I'm out on the stand
to play ♪
♪ Sunday mornin'
my head is bad ♪
♪ But it's worth it for
the times that I've had ♪
♪ But I've got to get my rest ♪
♪ 'Cause Monday's a mess ♪
♪ The big beat keep you rockin'
in your seat ♪
-NARRATOR: By the end of 1956,
all of the major
television networks
and Hollywood began to call.
And the entire nation
was tuning in.
-♪ The sun's gonna shine ♪
♪ In my back door some day ♪
♪ Just you wait and see ♪
♪ Girl can't help it ♪
♪ She was born to please ♪
♪ Can't help it, the girl
can't help it ♪
♪ And she's got a figure
made to squeeze ♪
♪ Can't help it, the girl
can't help it ♪
♪ And she's got a figure
made to squeeze ♪
♪ Can't help it, the girl
can't help it ♪
-Let's face it,
rhythm and blues, uh, is here.
So we have a man here today
who is just
about the hottest attraction
in that field.
As a matter of fact,
I have a -- have a little award
to present to him a bit later,
something I don't know
if he knows about yet.
The one and only Fats Domino.
-♪ When my dreamboat
comes home ♪
-BARTHOLOMEW: You wanna make
a good impression
because this means an awful lot
to you
to be on those type of shows.
You're not only help -- helpin'
them, you're helpin' yourself,
gettin' yourself exposure
all over the world.
So you think about that.
And you wanna do the best
you can.
-When Fats appeared on
network TV show,
it increased sales tremendously.
-Uh, Fats, as you know,
is one of our great disciples
of rock 'n' roll.
And Fats, according
to a clipping in "Down Beat,"
Dizzy Gillespie just
finished a tour
in the Middle East
where he was a smash.
-DOMINO: Crazy, man.
-And Louis Armstrong
was a big hit in South Africa.
-DOMINO: Crazy, man.
-And a rumor has it that
you're going to
introduce rock 'n' roll
to Alaska.
-DOMINO: Cool, man.
♪ I'm walkin', yes indeed ♪
♪ And I'm talkin'
about you and me ♪
♪ And I'm hopin'
you'll ask me back again ♪
-♪ I'm flyin', I'm flyin' high ♪
♪ I'm shy, me, oh, my ♪
♪ I'm hopin' you'll ask me
back again, again ♪
-♪ What you gonna do
when the well runs dry ♪
♪ You gonna run away tonight ♪
♪ I'm gonna run right by your
side ♪
♪ For you, Perry Como,
I'd even die ♪
♪♪
-COLEMAN: This is
November 18, 1956,
a very significant date,
a very cold night
in New York City
when Ed Sullivan
announced Fats Domino.
-ANNOUNCER:
"The Ed Sullivan Show."
-I had a lot
of respect for him.
He spent a lot of time with us.
He -- he -- he gave us his all.
And you know what I mean.
He would be with us
all day long.
And -- and that wasn't all.
And then he had us as many times
that we wanted to.
-...New Orleans,
another...
Well, he's had so many.
This... He's had 1 million
record, million sales record.
Here is Fats Domino
singing "Blueberry Hill."
So, let's hear it...
[Playing]
-COLEMAN: He put Fats' band
behind a curtain.
And he put Fats just playing
the piano by himself,
which was a very strange thing
for Fats.
And then even stranger was
at the very end of the show --
of the song, I should say,
Fats stood up.
It was kind of like Ed Sullivan
wanted people to see
how chubby he was so that,
you know, he looks harmless.
♪♪
-♪ For you were my thrill ♪
-One of the great record stars,
high on the list of all hits
in the country today,
is a very happy, little,
rotund fellow named Fats Domino.
-That was the beginning
of the "harmless
Fats Domino" mythology,
which still continues
to some degree today.
-Well, Fats, I have this
surprise for you now.
This is from "Cash Box,"
one of the important, uh, record
industry, uh, trade papers.
And they want you
to have this award
because you've been voted
by the Disc Jockeys of America
the most programmed
rhythm and blues male vocalist
of the year 1956.
Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
-NARRATOR: In 1957,
the Fats Domino band
traveled 30,000 miles
around the country,
working a total of 355 shows
and selling out nightclubs
and concert halls
everywhere they ventured.
-ALLEN: He was one
of the biggest stars out.
There was no other bigger star
than Fats in --
in the rock 'n' roll field.
-MAN: We -- we got to knock
and push 'em off of us.
You know, I mean, you know,
they --
they was just somethin' else.
They knock down the walls
to get to Fats Domino.
I'm not kiddin'.
They really did.
-RAY: I did a lot of travelin'.
Nothin' like bein'
with Fats Domino.
We'd drive and drive.
And I keep sayin', "Well,
aren't we gonna stop for lunch?
Aren't we gonna --
are we gonna eat?"
-McLEAN: You know, him and
his brother came in the house
and said, "No, we want
you to come and go to
Pensacola,
Florida with us.
We got to be there tonight."
I say, "It's Christmas.
I don't wanna go nowhere."
And you know what happened?
They took and carried me
and picked me up,
I'm helpless,
and put me on the bus.
And, you know, I was in Florida.
-BARTHOLOMEW:
That was my life out there.
A lot of times we was doin'
them one nighters,
all night long sleepin' in the
car and all that kinda (bleep).
-HARDESTY: The most fun was
after we got off in the hotels.
There was party,
party, party, parties goin'
on from the bottom
to the top floor.
-NARRATOR: With Fats'
enormous popularity,
promoters had little trouble
filling concert halls
and ballrooms to capacity.
White and black fans
clamored to see Fats live,
sometimes
with explosive results.
-COLEMAN: He had more riots
than any other
rock 'n' roller,
uh, maybe ever.
He had four major riots
at his shows,
partly because of integration
but also the fact that they
had alcohol at these shows.
So they were mixing alcohol
plus dancing
plus the races together
for the first time
in a lot of these places.
And it was leading
to a little fights
which soon bloomed
into huge fights.
And they called the police.
-HARDESTY: We got caught
in two riots.
And it wasn't --
it wasn't a racial thing.
There was a fight.
And with -- within the fight,
the police decided to throw
tear gas in the hall.
And everybody panic.
Well, it turned out
not to be a riot,
but people tryin'
to escape --
tryin' to get away from
the tear gas.
When they started broadcastin'
that there was --
where Fats Domino was playin'
and there was a race riot,
that was a $1 million
exposure right there.
All the news media picked it up.
So that was publicity.
But there...
It wasn't a real race riot.
-COMO: Fats, this
rock 'n' roll music seems to be
under an awful heavy attack
from all over the country.
There's been riots.
It's been banned
in certain parts of this country
and abroad.
You know of any reason for that?
-Well, as far as I know,
music make people happy.
I know it make me happy.
-COMO: You wouldn't blame it
on rock 'n' roll.
-No, indeed.
-What happened up in
Rhode Island
where you where playin'?
-Well, you know how it is when
the Navy and Marines
get together.
-You don't think
it was the music?
-No, couldn't be.
-NARRATOR: Life on the road
for an African-American
rock 'n' roll band, even
the country's most popular one,
was mired in the
pre-Civil Rights mores
of the day.
-DOMINO: Sometimes we used
to go up 100 mile out the way
to get a place to sleep.
-It was tough. We stayed in
little, small-like hotels.
We didn't have the privilege
and the -- the restaurants.
I started drivin' the bus.
And I would go
into these restaurants
or these places
and sort of help integration
along to push things, you know?
And when the hotels
first integrated, that was --
I was the first ones in them.
-Well, I think there is, uh,
no doubt about the fact that,
uh, the Negro
is more determined now than
ever before to be free.
I think that there is
a discontent
in the Negro community,
a frustration and an impatience,
if we can use that word, uh,
that we haven't seen before.
I've been around the country
for the last few days,
uh, speaking.
And I don't think
I've ever seen, uh,
the Negro population
of our nation
more aroused and more determined
as I've seen
on these particular trips.
-DIAMOND: Before
Martin Luther King got killed,
Fats was in that same hotel
2 weeks before then
playin' for the --
the garbage workers there.
He'd bring the --
the workers together when --
whenever he'd play,
white and black.
It's somethin' about his person
that draw a lot
of people in, you know.
-MAN: Once it was recognized,
once it accepted,
and once the -- the audience,
the people
started wantin' this music,
there was nothin'
that the radio stations
or television can do about it.
They had to accept it.
-COLEMAN: So there was
this historic moment
in American history
that -- that things
were kind of coming together.
And people don't really
credit rock 'n' roll
with integrating America.
But it really did.
-NARRATOR: Constantly far away
from his loving family
and his Ninth Ward home,
life on the road
was beginning to take its toll.
-DOMINO: Anybody,
when you first leave home,
especially New Orleans,
you still got your home
on your mind.
And the whole band is like that.
Every time I had a Monday night
off, I usually fly home.
-NARRATOR: Although he
received the adulation
of millions of fans,
Fats always longed to be
on that last stretch of highway
that led to the city he loved.
-♪ This time
I'm walkin' to New Orleans ♪
♪ I'm walkin' to New Orleans ♪
♪ I'm gonna need
two pair of shoes ♪
♪ When I get through walkin'
these blues ♪
♪ When I get back to
New Orleans ♪
♪ I've got my suitcase
in my hand ♪
♪ Now ain't that a shame ♪
♪ I'm leavin' here today ♪
♪ Yes, I'm goin' back home
to stay ♪
♪ Yes, I'm walkin' to
New Orleans ♪
♪ You used to be my honey ♪
♪ 'Til I lost all
my money ♪
♪ No use for me to cry ♪
♪ I'll see you
by and by ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm walkin'
to New Orleans ♪
♪ And I got no time
for talkin' ♪
♪ I'm walkin' to New Orleans ♪
-NARRATOR: By the end of 1963,
a new generation of rockers,
many of whom idolized Fats,
were grabbing
the world's attention.
Although Fats
continued to record,
his top-10 hit records
were now well behind him.
For the next 40 years,
he brought the big beat
around the world,
performing his hits
at sold-out shows
from New Orleans to Japan.
-♪ I'm walkin' ♪
♪ Yes, indeed
I'm walkin' ♪
-NARRATOR: Up until his final
public performance in 2006,
Dave Bartholomew
and Herb Hardesty
were often in the band.
For 65 years,
Fats never departed
from his boogie-woogie roots
and always ended his shows
with a gumbo-spiced ode
to New Orleans --
"When the Saints
Go Marchin' In."
-♪ Oh, when the saints ♪
♪ Go marchin' in ♪
♪ Oh, when the saints
go marchin' in ♪
-BARTHOLOMEW: Always close
with the saints.
Sometimes we couldn't get off
the bandstand, we'd go back.
-♪ When the saints go
marchin' in ♪
♪ Oh, when the sun ♪
♪ Refused to shine ♪
♪ Oh, when the sun
refused to shine ♪
-A gentlemen.
When you work
with a man 50 years,
that should speak for itself.
♪ Oh, when the saints ♪
♪ Go marchin' in ♪
♪ Oh, when the saints
go marchin' in ♪
-The stories he told
was so charmin',
even when he was tellin'
a hard luck story.
A prince of a man.
-♪ Oh, when the sun ♪
♪ Refused to shine ♪
♪ Oh, when the sun
refused to shine ♪
♪ I say I want to be
in that number ♪
-Colleges and universities
that had courses
only on jazz artists.
I can... Why not on --
on -- on artists
like Fats or Chuck Berry?
I can never understand why
the cities that they represented
didn't recognize them
the same way
they would recognize
a Louis Armstrong.
-COLEMAN: John Lennon,
the first song
he ever learned
was "Ain't That a Shame."
First rock 'n' roll song
that George Harrison ever heard
was "I'm in Love Again."
And Paul McCartney's
just recorded a slew
of Fats Domino songs.
Uh, on top of that,
Elvis Presley once even called
Fats the king of rock 'n' roll.
Little Richard said
that he worshipped Fats
and was honored
to touch his hand.
And, of course,
he recorded most of his hits
with members of Fats' band.
-Here you have a formula
that they haven't had to change
in over half a century.
It's as good now as it was then.
The music business changes
every week.
Here is something
that you're witnessing
and listening to the same sound
that music lovers would have
been hearing half a century ago.
And it still does the trick.
It does the trick
because it's really good.
-Two Daves, I don't
think that would have worked.
Uh, two Fats wouldn't have
gotten off the ground.
Two Fats would have had to find
another one Dave somewhere.
♪♪
-I'm glad
I could join the elites
and just be one in a crowd.
Together we stand,
divided we fall.
♪♪
NARRATOR:
Funding for "American Masters"
is provided by...
the Corporation
for Public Broadcasting...
Support for this program
also provided by
the National Endowment
for the Arts.
Art works.
The Paul W. Zuccaire Foundation,
and by contributions to your PBS
station from viewers like you.
Thank you.
MAN: You know, just gather
around quietly. ♪♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
NARRATOR:
To learn more about Fats Domino
and other American Masters,
visit pbs.org/americanmasters,
or find us on Facebook, Twitter,
and Tumblr.
♪♪
"The Big Beat: Fats Domino
and the Birth of Rock 'n' Roll"
is available on DVD.
To order, visit shopPBS.org
or call 1-800-PLAY-PBS.
DOMINO: Whoo!
♪♪
MAN: Antoine, you know,
you still got it, man.
DOMINO: You -- You --
You still got it, too.
[ Both laugh ]
♪ ♪
BE MORE PBS
[Glasses clink]
Narrator: Looking for a
traditional-style butcher shop?
Head over to
Stachowski's market
for a true old-world experience.
Jamie, how you doing?
Mr. Jonas, how are you?
Good to see you.
Yeah. Nice to see
you as always.
It's a pleasure.
What's good?
Narrator: Owner and head butcher
Jamie Stachowski
brings some serious flair
to his Georgetown storefront.
Stachowski:
We're a throwback.
This just reminds people of some
time back in their history--
a custom butcher shop,
where you can find
a variety of meat products
and things to go along
with them.
[Sizzling]
That's what we've tried
to achieve here,
is a corner candy store
for carnivores.
And let's do some
scallopini.
Just slice it,
maybe pound it
a little for me.
All right, terrific.
All right, so let me
get this sliced up
and pounded.
Jonas: There just aren't
places like this anymore,
where you have a local butcher,
a local meat store.
This is like Paris.
This is like
the Italian countryside.
There's a little bit of it
right here in Georgetown.
There's a nice feeling
to the place.
Narrator: Stop by at lunch
for one of the market's
signature sandwiches,
like the hot pastrami
or 4-meat grinder.
Just don't plan on
finishing it anytime soon.
Man: Oh, no. You really can't
eat the grinder in one sitting.
And if you can, make him
president of the United States.
I was surprised
when I received it,
because I literally
could eat this all week long.
So we had to
have it cut in 4s
just for me to be able
to take a bite.
Stachowski: You travel to
the Polish neighborhood
where I'm from,
sandwiches were meals to us,
so they tended to be
on the big side.
Look, we are in Georgetown,
but we're tucked up away
in the Rose Park neighborhood.
So we gotta stand out,
and our sandwiches
let us do that.
Now we've gotten
the reputation for that.
Narrator: And if your
appetite isn't so big,
there are still a few items
on the menu that might be
just the ticket.
Sometimes if you don't
feel like you can handle
3 days' worth of sandwich,
might just need a salad!
Narrator: To learn more
about "Neighborhood Eats,"
visit WETA.org.
Narrator: To learn more
about "Neighborhood Eats,"
NARRATOR:
From Earth to space.
There's no tougher 50 miles
to cross.
>> THIS IS "BBC WORLD NEWS
AMERICA."
FUNDING OF THIS PRESENTATION IS
MADE POSSIBLE BY
THE FREEMAN FOUNDATION,
AND KOVLER FOUNDATION, PURSUING
SOLUTIONS FOR AMERICA'S
NEGLECTED NEEDS.
>> WOW, THAT IS UNBELIEVABLE.
♪
>> I'M FLYING!
>> STAY CURIOUS.
♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> AND NOW, "BBC WORLD NEWS."
JANE: THIS IS "BBC WORLD NEWS
AMERICA."
REPORTING FROM WASHINGTON, I AM
JANE O'BRIEN.
CONGRESSIONAL DEMOCRATS ANNOUNCE
NEW INVESTIGATIONS INTO
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HE SAYS IT IS HARASSMENT.
REVEALING THE DARK SIDE OF
BRAZIL'S MINING INDUSTRY.
TOXIC WASTE IS BEING HELD BACK
BY DAMS THAT HAVE THE POTENTIAL
TO COLLAPSE.
>> IF THE WHOLE LOT BRAKES, ALL
THESE TOXINS COULD ENTER THE
WATER SUPPLY OF MILLIONS OF
PEOPLE.
JANE: BEHOLD THE ROVER.
SOON IT WILL BE HEADING TO MARS
BEARING THE NAME OF A
GROUNDBREAKING SCIENTIST.
JANE: WELCOME TO OUR VIEWERS ON
PUBLIC TELEVISION IN AMERICA AND
AROUND THE GLOBE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS BRACING
HIMSELF FOR A NEW WAVE OF
INVESTIGATIONS AFTER A WARNING
IN HIS STATE OF THE UNION SPEECH
THAT SUCH MOVES WOULD ONLY HARM
THE NATION.
DEMOCRATS ON KEY OVERSIGHT
COMMITTEES SAY THEY WILL DEMAND
HIS TAX RETURNS AS PART OF
BROADER INQUIRIES INTO HIS
BUSINESS DEALINGS.
THEY ARE ALSO REOPENING AN
INVESTIGATION INTO RUSSIAN
ELECTION MEDDLING AND POSSIBLE
COLLUSION BY THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN.
NOT SURPRISINGLY, THE PRESIDENT
IS FURIOUS.
TODAY HE TWEETED, "PRESIDENTIAL
HARASSMENT.
IT SHOULD NEVER BE ALLOWED TO
HAPPEN AGAIN."
I SPOKE A SHORT TIME AGO TO
SHANNON PETTYPIECE OF BLOOMBERG.
THERE ARE SO MANY
INVESTIGATIONS.
WHAT ARE THESE NEW
INVESTIGATIONS LOOKING FOR AND
WHAT MIGHT THEY FIND?
SHANNON: THERE ARE SO MANY, AND
THEY ARE SO BROAD AT THIS POINT.
THE DEMOCRATS HAVE NOT NARROWED
IT DOWN THE EXACT AREAS THEY
WILL PROBE.
THEY HAVE TALKED ABOUT
EVERYTHING FROM THE PRESIDENT'S
HOTEL IN WASHINGTON AND WHETHER
IT VIOLATES THE CONSTITUTION,
THEY HAVE TALKED ABOUT THE TAX
RETURNS, AS YOU MENTIONED, HIS
CONNECTIONS TO RUSSIA, HIS
INDIVIDUAL BUSINESS DEALINGS --
HIS HOTELS IN NEW YORK, PANAMA,
PROJECTS IN CANADA.
TO GO DEEP INTO HIS BUSINESS,
HIS PERSONAL FINANCES, INTO HIS
ADMINISTRATION.
AND THEN THERE IS ALL THE THINGS
THAT HAPPENED WHILE HE IS
PRESIDENT -- SECURITY
CLEARANCES, DEALINGS BY CABINET
SECRETARIES.
YES, IT COULD BE VERY BROAD.
THE DEMOCRATS HAVE NOT NAILED
DOWN THE FOCUS AND THEY HAVE TO
DO THAT IN THE NEXT MONTH OR SO
BECAUSE THEY HAVE LIMITED
RESOURCES.
JANE: HOW IS THIS GOING TO
AFFECT THE WORKINGS OF THE WHITE
HOUSE?
SHANNON: IT COULD REALLY DRAG A
LOT OF THE ADMINISTRATION TO A
HALT.
WHEN YOU TALK TO PAST WHITE
HOUSES -- THE CLINTON WHITE
HOUSE IS THE BEST PARALLEL TO
THIS -- THE CONSTANT DRUMBEAT OF
INVESTIGATIONS -- YOU HAVE THE
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL'S OFFICE
DEALING WITH A RESPONSE TO THE
SUBPOENAS.
PEOPLE WITH THE CLINTON
ADMINISTRATION TOLD ME THERE
BECOMES A GENERAL ANXIETY AND
CONCERN IN THE WHITE HOUSE -- AM
I GOING TO GET SUBPOENAED, THE
STAFFERS START THINKING.
THEY WORRY WHAT THEY SAID TO
SOMEONE AND WHAT RECORDS WERE
KEPT.
AS FAR AS THE NEWS CYCLE GOES
THERE WILL BE A DAILY DRUMBEAT
OF SUBPOENAS, TESTIMONIES, NEW
DOCUMENTS, AND THAT WILL
DISTRACT FROM THE AGENDA OF
OTHER THINGS THEY WOULD LIKE TO
GET DONE AND BE TALKING ABOUT.
JANE: PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS WARNED
IN THE PAST THAT IF THE
INVESTIGATIONS CROSSED A RED
LINE, HE MIGHT DO SOMETHING
ABOUT IT.
WHAT CAN HE DO?
SHANNON: WHEN IT COMES TO
CONGRESS, NOT THAT MUCH.
THAT IS WHY THIS SORT OF MAKES
THE ROBERT MUELLER INVESTIGATION
LOOK LIKE A WARMUP ROUND.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT CONGRESS,
SEPARATE BRANCH OF GOVERNMENT,
AND THE ABILITY IT HAS AND THE
LARGE SUBPOENA POWER IT HAS,
THERE IS NOT MUCH HE CAN DO.
HE CAN FIGHT BACK INSIDE -- HE
CAN FIGHT BACK AND CITE
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE ON SOME
THINGS AND PUSH BACK ON
SUBPOENAS, SAYING THAT THEY ARE
IRRELEVANT, YOU ARE GOING AFTER
PRIVATE COMPANIES.
BUT CONGRESS DOES HAVE HER BROAD
INVESTIGATIVE POWERS.
HE HAS SEPARATE INVESTIGATIONS
TO WORRY ABOUT -- NEW YORK IN
THE SOUTHERN DISTRICT, OUTSIDE
OF HIS CONTROL, CONTINUING TO
PURSUE THINGS WITH HIS INAUGURAL
COMMITTEE, THE LATEST EXAMPLE OF
SOMEPLACE THEY HAVE BEEN LOOKING
AT.
JANE: HE HAS ALREADY TWEETED.
HOW ELSE MIGHT HE REACT?
SHANNON: THE TWEET IS
INTERESTING BECAUSE HE IS
STARTING TO PICK A FIGHT BEFORE
THE FIGHT HAS BEGUN, SOMETHING
HE TENDS TO DO.
YES, THE DEMOCRATS HAVE TALKED
BROADLY ABOUT WHAT THEY WANT TO
INVESTIGATE, BUT IT IS NOT LIKE
50 SUBPOENAS HAVE LANDED IN THE
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL'S OFFICE,
NOT LIKE THEY HAD DEMANDED HIS
SON COME IN FOR A PUBLIC
HEARING.
THERE IS POTENTIAL FOR ALL OF
THAT TO HAPPEN, BUT HE HAS GONE
OUT AHEAD.
WHAT THAT DOES IS POKE THE BEAR.
IT GOES AFTER THE COMMITTEES AND
RLES THEM UP, AND SOME MEMBERS
FEEL LIKE THEY HAVE TO
INVESTIGATE JUST TO SHOW THEM
-- HIM THAT THEY HAVE THAT POWER
AND THAT ABILITY TO DO SO.
JANE: SHANNON PETTYPIECE, THANKS
VERY MUCH INDEED FOR JOINING ME.
THE POLITICAL CRISIS IN VIRGINIA
IS DEEPENING AMID ALLEGATIONS OF
RACIAL AND SEXUAL MISCONDUCT BY
THE STATE'S LEADERS.
THE THREE TOP DEMOCRATS ARE IN
HOT WATER, BUT SO FAR THERE ARE
NO SIGNS THEY ARE STEPPING DOWN,
AND THE STORY DOESN'T END THERE.
THE IMAGES IN THE 1968 YEARBOOK
OF THE PRESTIGIOUS VIRGINIA
MILITARY INSTITUTE ARE SHOCKING.
IT HAS BEEN REPORTED THAT THE
-- THAT TOMMY NORMENT, THE STATE
SENATE MAJORITY LEADER, WAS THE
EDITOR AT THE TIME.
HE HAS DISTANCED HIMSELF, SAYING
HE DID NOT OVERSEE EVERY PAGE OF
THE PUBLICATION.
MEANWHILE, TWO OF HER VIRGINIA'S
TOP THREE DEMOCRATS HAVE
ADMITTED TO PAST RACIST
BEHAVIOR, AND THE LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR IS ACCUSED OF SEXUAL
ASSAULT.
JUSTIN FAIRFAX DENIES THE
ALLEGATIONS, BUT HIS ACCUSER,
VANESSA TYSON, HAS GIVEN NEW
DETAILS OF THE ENCOUNTER IN
2004.
IN A STATEMENT, SHE SAID,
"CONSENSUAL KISSING QUICKLY
TURNED INTO A SEXUAL ASSAULT."
FAIRFAX DESCRIBED HER ACCOUNT AS
PAINFUL, BUT SAID, "I HAVE NEVER
DONE ANYTHING LIKE WHAT SHE
SUGGESTS."
NATIONAL DEMOCRATS HAVE ADOPTED
ZERO-TOLERANCE OF MEN ACCUSED OF
SEXUAL MISCONDUCT.
THEY HAVE CALLED FOR AN
INVESTIGATION OF THE
ALLEGATIONS, BUT FEW HAVE
DEMANDED FURTHER ACTION YET.
>> THIS HAS BEEN AN AWFUL WEEK
FOR VIRGINIA.
JANE: GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM,
WHOSE COLLEGE YEARBOOK PHOTO
STARTED THE CRISIS, IS REFUSING
TO RESIGN.
STATE ATTORNEY GENERAL MARK
HERRING, WHO ADMITTED WEARING
BLACKFACE AT A PARTY IN THE
1980'S, IS ALSO STAYING PUT FOR
NOW.
VIRGINIA IS A KEY POLITICAL
BATTLEGROUND, BUT THE CRISIS
THREATENS TO WEAKEN DEMOCRATS
AHEAD OF STATE ELECTIONS IN
NOVEMBER AND NEXT YEAR'S
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION, WHEN THEY
WILL TRY TO DRAW A BRIGHT LINE
BETWEEN THEIR CANDIDATE AND
DONALD TRUMP.
FOR MORE ON THE UPHEAVAL IN THE
STATE, MY COLLEAGUES KATTY KAY
AND CHRISTIAN FRASER SPOKE TO
LARRY SABATO, DIRECTOR OF THE
CENTER OF POLITICS AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA, AND THEY
STARTED BY ASKING HIM ABOUT THE
CURRENT LEVEL OF CHAOS.
LARRY: WHAT IS HAPPENING HERE IS
THAT THE ENTIRE ELECTED
SUPERSTRUCTURE OF THE STATE IS
NOW INVOLVED IN VARIOUS
SCANDALS, AND WE JUST ADDED ONE.
THE REPUBLICAN MAJORITY LEADER
OF THE STATE SENATE.
SO IT IS NOW OFFICIALLY A
BIPARTISAN SCANDAL.
CHRISTIAN: AS I UNDERSTAND IT,
LARRY, IF ALL THESE THREE
DEMOCRATS WERE TO STEP DOWN, THE
NEXT IN LINE TO BECOME GOVERNOR
WOULD BE THE HOUSE SPEAKER, WHO
IS A REPUBLICAN.
LARRY: THAT IS RIGHT, AND THAT
IS WHY IT WON'T HAPPEN.
THE PEOPLE OF VIRGINIA VOTED
OVERWHELMINGLY, REALLY IN
LANDSLIDE PROPORTIONS, FOR
DEMOCRATS IN 2017, AND THAT WAS
TRUE FOR ALL THREE OF THEM.
THAT WON'T HAPPEN BECAUSE IT IS
CONTRARY TO THE POPULAR WILL AND
IT WOULD BE SEEN AS A KIND OF
SILENT COUP.
THE PEOPLE WHO INSTIGATED SOME
OF THESE CHARGES ARE CLEARLY
CONNECTED TO THE REPUBLICAN
PARTY AND SOME VERY CONSERVATIVE
WEBSITES.
SO IT IS JUST NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN.
THEY WILL FIND SOME WAY TO
STAGGER RESIGNATIONS, IF IT EVEN
COMES TO RESIGNATION, SO THAT A
DEMOCRAT WILL SUCCEED TO THE
GOVERNORSHIP, A DEMOCRAT WHO CAN
STAY THERE.
KATTY: LARRY, I WANT TO ASK YOU
ABOUT JUSTIN FAIRFAX IN A
SECOND, BUT FIRST OF ALL, THIS
ISSUE OF RACE AND VIRGINIA AND
TO WHAT EXTENT THE ACCUSATIONS
AGAINST THE TWO DEMOCRATS WHO
HAVE BEEN ACCUSED OF BLACKENING
THEIR FACES, TO WHAT EXTENT IS
THAT REPRESENTATIVE OF
VIRGINIA'S FAIRLY RECENT RACIAL
PAST?
LARRY: I THINK IT IS ALL TOO
REPRESENTATIVE, TO BE BLUNT
ABOUT IT.
I WAS BORN IN THIS STATE AND
GREW UP ABOUT A DECADE PRIOR TO
THE TWO DEMOCRATS WHO ARE IN
TROUBLE RIGHT NOW FOR BLACKFACE.
I HATE TO ADMIT IT, BUT EVEN AT
MY OWN UNIVERSITY THERE HAVE
BEEN SUBSTANTIAL INCIDENTS OF
BLACKFACE OVER THE YEARS, AND
IN FACT, ONE OF THE DEMOCRATS
WHO IS IN TROUBLE BECAUSE OF
BLACKFACE USED IT AS AN
UNDERGRADUATE STUDENT AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA.
SO IT IS NOT JUST HERE, IT IS
EVERYWHERE.
WE ARE FINDING PHOTOS IN A JUST
ABOUT ALL OF THE COLLEGE
YEARBOOKS.
SO THIS IS A PROBLEM THAT
PROBABLY IS GENERIC IN THE
SOUTH, BUT RIGHT NOW THE FOCUS
IS ON VIRGINIA, AND IT POINTS
UP THE VERY DIFFICULT
RELATIONSHIP WE'VE HAD AMONG THE
RACES IN VIRGINIA, AND EVEN
THOUGH WE HAVE MADE PROGRESS, WE
HAVE PROBABLY MADE LESS PROGRESS
THAN WE THINK.
KATTY: OK, SO IF THE
RELATIONSHIPS BETWEEN RACES WERE
NOT TRICKY ENOUGH, THIS STORY IS
ALSO HIGHLIGHTING THE
RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN GENDERS AS
WELL, BECAUSE THE NUMBER TWO
DEMOCRAT, AN AFRICAN-AMERICAN,
HAS BEEN ACCUSED OF HARASSMENT.
I WANT TO READ WHAT HIS ACCUSER,
VANESSA TYSON, SAID, "WHAT
STARTED AS CONSENSUAL KISSING
QUICKLY TURNED INTO SEXUAL
ASSAULT."
SHOULD GOES ON TO -- SHE GOES ON
TO GIVE A GRAPHIC ACCOUNT OF
BEING FORCED TO PERFORM ORAL SEX
ON JUSTIN FAIRFAX.
HE DENIES IT AND SAID, "I TAKE
THIS SITUATION SERIOUSLY AND
CONTINUE TO BELIEVE DR. TYSON
SHOULD BE TREATED WITH RESPECT,
BUT I CANNOT AGREE WITH A
DESCRIPTION OF EVENTS THAT IS
SIMPLY NOT TRUE."
WHERE DOES THIS LEAVE NUMBER TWO
DEMOCRAT JUSTIN FAIRFAX?
IN THE ERA OF ME TOO, LARRY, IN
THE POST-BRETT KAVANAUGH PERIOD,
WHERE DOES THIS LEAVE HIM?
LARRY: IT LEAVES HIM IN DEEP
TROUBLE AND DAMAGED FOR THE
FUTURE, EVEN IF THIS CANNOT BE
PROVEN ONE WAY OR THE OTHER, AND
IT PROBABLY CAN'T.
THIS WAS 2004 AND THERE WERE NO
TEMPORARY WITNESSES -- NO
CONTEMPORARY WITNESSES OR
CONTEMPORANEOUS TESTIMONY.
ALTHOUGH THE SENIOR
AFRICAN-AMERICAN OFFICEHOLDER IN
VIRGINIA, CONGRESSMAN BOBBY
SCOTT, TODAY HE SAID HE KNEW
SOME OF IT WAS TRUE.
HE HAD DATED THIS WOMAN A COUPLE
OF YEARS AGO AND HAD HEARD THE
ACCOUNT THEN.
SO LESS THAN A WEEK AGO, THIS
AFRICAN-AMERICAN NUMBER TWO IN
VIRGINIA WAS ON THE VERGE OF
TAKING THE OATH OF OFFICE AS
GOVERNOR.
NOW HE IS GOING TO BE VERY LUCKY
TO FINISH HIS TERM AS LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR, AND HIS FUTURE IS
CLOUDY.
JANE: LARRY SABATO FROM THE
UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA.
A LOOK AT SOME OF THE DAY'S
OTHER NEWS.
THE UNITED NATIONS INQUIRY INTO
THE MURDER  OF JOURNALIST
JAMAL KHASHOGGI SAID HE WAS THE
VICTIM OF A BRUTAL AND
PREMEDITATED KILLING CARRIED OUT
BY SAUDI ARABIAN STATE
OFFICIALS.
IT ACCUSES SAUDI ARABIA OF
UNDERMINING EFFORTS TO
INVESTIGATE THE MURDER WHICH
TOOK PLACE IN THE SAUDI
CONSULATE IN ISTANBUL.
THE HEAD OF THE SOCIAL-MEDIA
PLATFORM INSTAGRAM HAS PLEDGED
TO REMOVE ALL GRAPHIC IMAGES OF
SELF HARM.
THE PROMISE MADE TO THE BBC
COMES AFTER THE FATHER OF A
14-YEAR-OLD BRITISH GIRL WHO
TOOK HER OWN LIFE ASSERTED THAT
INSTAGRAM HELPED KILL HIS
DAUGHTER.
THE HOSPITAL TREATING BRAZILIAN
PRESIDENT JAIR BOLSONARO SAYS HE
IS SUFFERING FROM PNEUMONIA.
MR. BOLSONARO NEARLY DIED AFTER
BEING STABBED IN THE ABDOMEN
DURING THE PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION
CAMPAIGN LAST YEAR.
HE HAS BEEN IN HOSPITAL FOR THE
PAST 12 DAYS AFTER A SECOND
ROUND OF SURGERY.
IT IS NOT CLEAR WHEN HE WILL BE
WELL ENOUGH TO BE DISCHARGED.
BRAZIL SUFFERED ONE OF THE
COUNTRY'S WORST-EVER
ENVIRONMENTAL DISASTERS LAST
MONTH WHEN A DAM AT A MINE
COLLAPSED, FLOODING THE AREA
WITH SLUDGE.
NEARLY 150 ARE KNOWN TO HAVE
DIED, WITH MANY MORE STILL
MISSING.
MUCH OF THE ATTENTION HAS
FOCUSED ON THE MINE OWNERS, VALE
, AND THE POOR SAFETY STANDARDS.
BUT SOME BLAME THE POWERFUL
MINING INDUSTRY AS A WHOLE AND
INADEQUATE GOVERNMENT
REGULATION.
FOR THIS REPORT, THE BBC'S
SCIENCE EDITOR DAVID SHUKMAN
WENT TO A TOWN NOT FAR FROM THE
DISASTER SCENE.
DAVID: WE TRAVELED TO THE HEART
OF BRAZIL'S IRON COUNTRY TO
INVESTIGATE THE DARK SIDE OF THE
MINES THAT THE INDUSTRY PREFERS
TO KEEP HIDDEN.
WE COME ACROSS A LURIDLY COLORED
STREAM, A FIRST CLUE ABOUT THE
POLLUTION CREATED IN THESE
HILLS.
SUDDENLY WE GET THIS RARE
GLIMPSE OF ONE OF THE LARGEST
MINING DUMPS IN BRAZIL.
IT IS FULL OF THE SAME KIND OF
SLUDGE THAT FLOODED OUT AND
KILLED SO MANY PEOPLE, A
BYPRODUCT THAT ACCUMULATES DAY
AFTER DAY FROM A MASSIVE
BUSINESS.
THE REASON THESE PLACES EXIST IS
WHEN YOU DIG OR OUT OF THE
GROUND, YOU ONLY WANT A TINY
FRACTION OF THE ROCK, THE METAL
THAT YOU ARE AFTER -- IN THIS
CASE, IRON.
THE REST YOU HAVE JUST GOT TO
GET RID OF, AND THE CHEAPEST WAY
TO DO THAT IS TO BUILD PLACES
LIKE THIS.
THE PROBLEM IS THEY ARE NOT
TEMPORARY.
THEY ARE MEANT TO LAST FOREVER.
THIS TOWERING STRUCTURE HOLDS
THE SLUDGE BACK, A DAM MADE OF
LAYERS OF MINING WASTE.
THERE ARE NEARLY 800 OF THESE IN
BRAZIL, AND MANY SAY THEY ARE
FAR TOO WEAK.
PEOPLE LIVING IN THE SHADOW OF
THE BARRIER HAVE CREATED THIS
COMPUTER SIMULATION OF HOW THEIR
HOMES COULD BE OVERWHELMED.
WHEN THE DAM DISINTEGRATED LAST
MONTH, IT LEFT OF THEM MORE
SCARED THAN EVER.
>> I DON'T SLEEP ANYMORE SINCE
WHAT HAPPENED.
IT WAS A WARNING.
IF THE SAME WERE TO HAPPEN HERE,
IN THREE YEARS, LESS THAN THREE
YEARS, TOMORROW, LATER, I DON'T
KNOW.
THE FEAR IS CONSTANT.
DAVID: NO CAMERA, NO VIDEO, NO
MONITORING.
NOT FAR AWAY, CAMPAIGNERS LEAD
ME TO ANOTHER SOURCE OF FEAR, AN
OLD GOLD LINE THAT HAS BEEN
-- AN OLD GOLD MINE THAT HAS
BEEN ABANDONED.
THE MACHINERY IS RUSTING.
THERE ARE POOLS OF LIQUID.
YOU GET ARSENIC AND CYANIDE WITH
GOLD-MINING.
IT IS MUCH MORE TOXIC THAN
MINING IRON ORE, AND THE WASTE
IS FAR MORE DANGEROUS.
THE LAST OWNERS OF THE MINE LEFT
A LEGACY THAT IS POISONOUS, A
MOUNTAIN OF CONTAMINATED DUST
AND ROCK, AND THE IMPACT OF ALL
OF THIS BEING RELEASED WOULD
BE DEVASTATING.
WHAT IS TRULY SHOCKING ABOUT
THIS PLACE IS THAT YOU HAVE THIS
HUGE LOAD OF HIGHLY TOXIC WASTE
HELD BACK BY A DAM I AM STANDING
ON THAT LITERALLY NO ONE IS
MAINTAINING.
RIGHT BESIDE IT, THIS LAKE OF
HIGHLY TOXIC LIQUID, ALSO HELD
BACK BY A DAM NO ONE IS LOOKING
AFTER.
IF THE WHOLE LOT BREAKS, ALL OF
THESE TOXINS COULD ENTER THE
WATER SUPPLY FOR MILLIONS OF
PEOPLE.
THE MINE IS IN AN AREA THAT IS A
VITAL SOURCE OF WATER.
A MAJOR CITY DEPENDS ON IT.
>> IF A VERY HEAVY RAIN FALLS,
WHO IS GOING TO GUARANTEE THAT
THIS DAM WON'T COLLAPSE?
IT IS REALLY SERIOUS.
DAVID: SO, DOWNSTREAM THERE IS A
RISK OF THE WATER BECOMING
TOXIC.
THIS SCIENTIST SAYS THE BROKEN
DAM HIGHLIGHTED WHAT COULD GO
WRONG.
>> I KNOW THE IMPORTANCE OF THE
WATER IN THIS PLACE FOR ALL THE
PEOPLE.
ALL THE CITIES AROUND THE MINE.
DAVID: BACK AT THE GOLD MINE, A
PITIFUL SIGHT, EMACIATED HORSES.
LIKE THE DAM, IT SEEMS NO ONE
CARES FOR THEM.
THERE ARE IDEAS FOR MAKING THESE
PLACES SAFE, BUT THERE ARE SO
MANY OF THEM, WHICH MEANS MORE
DISASTERS ARE WAITING TO HAPPEN.
DAVID SHUKMAN, BBC NEWS, IN
BRAZIL.
JANE: YOU ARE WATCHING "BBC
WORLD NEWS AMERICA."
STILL TO COME ON TONIGHT'S
PROGRAM, THE BRITISH PUBLIC HAS
SPOKEN.
THE NAME OF THE NEW MARS ROVER
WILL HONOR SCIENTIST ROSALIND
FRANKLIN.
20,000 DEAD OR DYING BIRDS HAVE
BEEN WASHED UP ON BEACHES ALONG
THE DUTCH COAST.
THEY ALL SHOWED SIGNS OF SEVERE
STARVATION.
SOME FEAR THERE WAS -- THAT IS
STILL FOR MUCH OF LAST MONTH
CAUSED THE DEATHS.
SOME OF THEM MAY HAVE BEEN
TRANSPORTING HAZARDOUS
MATERIALS.
A WARNING, YOU MAY FIND SOME OF
THESE IMAGES DISTRESSING.
REPORTER: THIS IS JUST ONE OF
THOUSANDS WASHED UP ON THE
BEACHES.
THE MASSIVE DEATHS HERE ON THE
DUTCH COAST HAVE BAFFLED
SCIENTISTS WHO ARE PURSUING
THREE MAIN LINES OF INQUIRY --
THE BIRDS MAY HAVE EATEN PLASTIC
, THEY COULD HAVE BEEN POISONED
BY CARAVAN LEAKING INTO THE SEA,
OR THAT HAZARDOUS CHEMICALS MAY
HAVE SOAKED INTO THEIR FEATHERS
FROM AFFECTING THEIR ABILITY TO
HUNT AND INSULATE THEMSELVES
FROM THE WATER.
A BIOLOGIST AND SEABIRD
SPECIALIST IS LEADING THE
INVESTIGATION.
>> YOUNG AND IN VERY BAD SHAPE.
EVEN ON THE OUTSIDE IT IS REALLY
SKINNY.
REPORTER: THE BIRDS FEED MOSTLY
ON FISH.
THE SEA IS RICH IN BASS AND
HERRING.
FOOD SHORTAGES ARE UNLIKELY.
BAD WEATHER MAY HAVE
CONTRIBUTED, BUT THAT DOES NOT
EXPLAIN WHY THE DEATHS ARE
LIMITED TO THE NETHERLANDS AND'S
POPULATION.
-- AND THIS PREPARATION.
>> IF IT IS INGESTED, IT SHOULD
STILL BE IN THE STOMACH BECAUSE
IT DOESN'T DIGEST.
REPORTER: THE SCIENTISTS HOPE
THAT MASS POSTMORTEMS ON THE
BIRDS WILL REVEAL WHAT IS
CAUSING THE DEATHS BEYOND ANY
REASONABLE DOUBT.
JANE: INTERNATIONAL PRESSURE IS
MOUNTING ON NICOLAS MADURO AS
THE CRISIS IN VENEZUELA
CONTINUES.
LEADERS FROM EUROPE AND LATIN
AMERICA HAVE SAID IT IS CRUCIAL
TO RESTORE DEMOCRACY AFTER
DISPUTED ELECTIONS RESULTED IN
JUAN GUAIDO DECLARING HIMSELF
INTERIM PRESIDENT.
AS THE POWER STRUGGLE PLAYS OUT
THERE, IT IS CLEAR MANY ORDINARY
VENEZUELANS ARE STRUGGLING TO
GET BY.
OUR CORRESPONDENT JAMES REYNOLDS
TOOK A RIDE ON A BUS THROUGH THE
CAPITAL, CARACAS, TO FIND OUT
HOW THEY ARE TRYING TO COPE.
JANE: JAMES REYNOLDS TALKING TO
VENEZUELANS ON A BUS ABOUT THE
CRISIS IN CARACAS.
SHE WAS A PIONEER IN SCIENCE,
AND THE NEW MARS ROVER WILL BEAR
THE NAME OF ROSALIND FRANKLIN.
OVER 30,000 PEOPLE ACROSS EUROPE
TOOK PART IN THE NAMING
COMPETITION, AND THE CHOSEN NAME
WAS UNVEILED EARLIER TODAY.
REBECCA MORELLE WAS THERE AND
SHE SENT THIS REPORT.
REBECCA: I AM HERE WHERE THIS
PROTOTYPE ROVER HEADS BEEN PUT
THROUGH ITS PACES.
IT IS DESIGNED TO ROAM ACROSS
THE ROCKET MARTIAN TERRAIN.
THE MISSION IS NEARLY COMPLETE
BUT ONE ELEMENT IS MISSING, AND
ITS NAME HAS BEEN REVEALED.
IT HAS BEEN NAMED TO DAVID --
NAMED TO THE ROSALIND FRANKLIN
ROVER.
>> ROSALIND FRANKLIN, A GREAT
BRITISH SCIENTIST WHO DID SO
MUCH TO UNLOCK THE SECRETS TO
HUMAN LIFE WITH THE DOUBLE
HELIX, IT IS ONLY FITTING THAT
THE MARS ROVER IS NAMED AFTER
ROSALIND BECAUSE IT WILL BE
SEARCHING FOR SIGNS OF PAST LIFE
ON MARS.
REBECCA: YOU GOT THE PUBLIC
INVOLVED IN THE NAMING PROCESS.
>> THE COMPETITION WAS OPEN UP
TO THE PUBLIC, 36,000 ENTRIES
HUGE RESPONSE.
IT SHOWS THERE IS SO MUCH PUBLIC
APPETITE FOR THESE EXPLORATION
MISSIONS.
REBECCA: IT REALLY IS A BIG
MISSION FOR THE EUROPEAN SPACE
AGENCY.
WHY IS IT SO VITAL?
>> IT IS A REALLY EXCITING
MISSION.
THIS ROVER IS GOING TO DRILL TWO
METERS UNDER THE SURFACE OF
MARS, AND THAT IS WHERE WE STAND
THE BEST CHANCE OF DISCOVERING
ORGANIC MOLECULES THAT COULD
HAVE RESIDED ON MARS.
IT GOES TO A SPECIAL LANDING
SITE, WHERE THERE WAS ONCE A
LIQUID OCEAN.
WE KNOW THAT 3.7 BILLION YEARS
AGO, EARTH AND MARS WERE
SIMILAR.
LIFE COULD HAVE EVOLVED ON MARS
AS WELL.
REBECCA: THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THIS IS OBVIOUSLY A ROBOTIC
MISSION HEADING TO MARS.
THE REAL THING HAS BEEN
ASSEMBLED AND SCIENTISTS ARE
WORKING AROUND THE CLOCK.
IT REALLY WILL BE A FITTING
HONOR FOR THE WOMAN WHO TRULY
WAS AN UNSUNG HERO OF SCIENCE TO
HAVE THIS LEGACY THAT WILL NOW
LIVE ON MARS.
JANE: REBECCA MORELLE REPORTING
THERE ON THE ONGOING QUEST.
YOU CAN FIND MORE ON ALL THE
DAY'S NEWS ON OUR WEBSITE.
TO SEE WHAT WE'RE WORKING ON AT
ANY TIME, CHECK OUT TWITTER.
I AM JANE O'BRIEN.
THANKS FOR WATCHING "BBC WORLD
NEWS AMERICA."
>> WITH THE BBC NEWS APP, OUR
VERTICAL VIDEOS ARE DESIGNED TO
WORK AROUND YOUR LIFESTYLE, SO
YOU CAN SWIPE YOUR WAY THROUGH
THE NEWS OF THE DAY AND STAY
UP-TO-DATE WITH THE LATEST
HEADLINES YOU CAN TRUST.
DOWNLOAD NOW FROM SELECTED APP
STORES.
>> FUNDING OF THIS PRESENTATION
IS MADE POSSIBLE BY
THE FREEMAN FOUNDATION,
AND KOVLER FOUNDATION, PURSUING
SOLUTIONS FOR AMERICA'S
NEGLECTED NEEDS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> POSSIBILITIES.
YOUR DAY IS FILLED WITH THEM.
>> TV, PLAY "DOWNTON ABBEY."
>> AND PBS HELPS EVERYONE
DISCOVER THEIRS.
ANYTIME, ANYWHERE.
PBS.
WE ARE WITH YOU FOR LIFE.
>> "BBC WORLD NEWS" WAS
PRESENTED BY KCET, LOS ANGELES.
>> Announcer:
- You try to pull
the technical defense.
"I was at my apartment,
I don't live there."
(woman)
- No.
- You could easily have said,
"I co-hosted the party,
and I told the police that
and that's why I'm here."
So, baby, you had to bring your
mother to court today, huh?
- I did.
- Are you still
spoon-feeding him or not?
Did you know that you could not
park there with a placard?
- I only parked
there 30 seconds.
- You were there 30 seconds?
- 30-45 seconds, ah...
- You keep talking,
they're gonna
take your
handicap placard away.
(announcer)
- This is the courtroom
of Judge Frank Caprio,
where people and cases
are met with compassion.
A different kind of judge.
A courtroom
like no other.
This is "Caught in Providence."
(Judge Caprio)
- Nicholas Damon.
- Good morning, Your Honor.
(Judge Caprio)
- Okay, Mr. Damon,
you're charged with
going through a red light
on Roger Williams Avenue
and Elmwood Avenue
at 10:18 in the morning.
Is this your
lawyer with you?
- This is my mother.
- I'm his mom.
- When are you gonna stop
taking care of these kids?
- I don't know.
- How long does it take
before you cut the cord?
- Never.
(Judge Caprio)
- That's a good answer.
- Now...
this is a classic case,
Inspector Quinn,
of a mother coming
to court for her little boy.
- Yup, it's her baby.
She's here for
her baby.
(Judge Caprio)
- She's here for her baby.
"I have to go to court
for my baby."
Do you have any
younger than him?
- No, no.
- No, only child.
(Judge Caprio)
- So he's your baby.
- He's my baby, yeah,
he's my only one.
- So, baby, you had to bring
your mother to court today, huh?
- I did, I did.
(Judge Caprio chuckling)
Hopefully it helps.
- Are you still spoon-feeding
him or not?
- No.
(Judge Caprio)
- No?
Well, he's...
he's charged with
going through a red light.
We're gonna look at it.
- Good.
- What is your name?
- Kerri.
- Damon.
Well, come up here.
Come up here,
come up here.
- You know, it's not
gonna end well for you,
so get rid of that smile.
- Get over here.
- Okay.
- We're gonna--
you've gotta give me a hand
on deciding this case, okay?
- Okay, all right.
- You've gotta be honest.
- I will be honest, yeah.
- All right.
- No special leniency.
- All right, so, okay, so--
- He hasn't had any...
- All right,
so I'm gonna get over here,
you're gonna get
over here,
and we're gonna look
at the video right here.
Okay, Lisa, let's go.
The light is red.
And...
- Uh... I thought it was
a right on red.
(Judge Caprio)
- Hold on for a minute.
The light is red.
He's coming down.
And he made
a right-hand turn.
Okay, now, what do you wanna
tell me about that?
- Well, he did
have his brakes on.
(attendees laughing)
And it was a slow,
it was a slow...
- You... you can take
a right turn on red over there.
It does have a sign
that says--
- I'm talking to your mother.
- All right, all right,
sorry.
- Be careful.
- I guess it was
a rolling stop.
- It was a rolling stop.
You don't
think he stopped.
(Kerri)
- Um...
No, he didn't
stop completely, no.
- You agree with that,
Inspector Quinn?
- She took the words
right out of my mouth, Judge.
(Judge Caprio)
- Yeah?
So what do you
think we should do with him?
- Um...
I don't know, I've done
a lot to him already
and screamed
at him about it,
and I-- I don't--
- Did you
beat him up?
- I didn't beat
him up.
No, I couldn't...
- Wanna use this?
- I could use this.
(attendees laughing)
- All right.
Like every mother,
like every mother, right,
she sees the good
in her son, right?
You're still her
little baby.
You can make
a right-hand turn on red.
At this location
you had to stop.
Your mother says
your brakes were on
and that you came
to a rolling stop,
so the question is--
she's making
an impassioned plea
that you made an attempt
to stop
and that
it was a close call.
Is that what you
were saying?
- That's what
I was saying, yes.
- So how do you wanna
find him?
Guilty or not guilty?
- Uh, I would
find him not guilty.
(attendees laughing)
- Surprise.
It's a big surprise,
Inspector Quinn.
- I'm totally shocked
on that ruling, Judge.
- All right, I asked for it,
so I guess you're gonna
be found not guilty.
Good luck to you.
- Thank you so much.
- All right, take care.
♪♪
(Judge Caprio)
- Daniel Ferreras.
Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
(Judge Caprio)
- You have a parking ticket
on Salisbury Street.
- Yeah.
- This is parking
in a prohibited area.
Now, listen, hold on a second.
All right, good.
We have two mics.
You are between
both of them.
Get to one or the other.
Get close,
get closer to the mic.
- Like that?
- Perfect.
Okay, what do you
wanna tell me?
You have a handicap placard.
- I missing
the ticket.
I... I'm no more
here for that.
But I go over to the...
to have
a handicap ticket.
Says $90.
It's too much for me.
- Mr. Ferreras,
a handicap...
placard allows you
to park in the handicap zone.
- Mm-hmm.
- It also allows you to park
at a parking meter
without putting
money in the meter.
- No have a meter,
nothing like that.
- I know.
It also allows
you to park
in a timed zone.
It does not allow
you to park
in a sign that
says "no parking."
Did you know that you could
not park there
with the placard?
- I only park there
30 seconds, sir.
- You were there 30 seconds?
- Yeah.
- All right, wait,
hold on for a minute.
- 30 seconds is up.
- Yes.
(Judge Caprio)
- You parked that far.
You get out of the car,
what did you do?
- I pick up
my daughter for the house
and outside, that's it.
- You went to your
daughter's house, all right...
and then you came
back out.
(Daniel)
- Yeah.
- And that took 30 seconds.
- From my car--
my car is 30--
(Judge Caprio)
- You took 30 seconds.
Right, you got out,
you ran
and got right back in.
Inspector Quinn, this guy's
the fastest guy in the country.
- I was gonna say, it takes
me about 30 seconds
to shut the car off,
open the car door,
shake it off
a little bit and get out.
- Inspector Quinn, he's got
a handicap placard.
You wanna give
him some leniency?
- Yes, Your Honor.
We wouldn't, uh...
We'll move to dismiss
with the warning,
advising him
about the legal spot.
I just wanna check the date
on that handicap.
- Mr. Ferreras, listen to me.
- Yes.
- All right,
just so you know...
... you said it took me
30 seconds
to go in the house...
see my daughter
and come back out.
You're handicapped.
- No, no, no, no,
no, to see my daughter--
- You've got a cane.
- I put daughter back
on fifth floor and go back.
- Yeah, I know, you went in,
you came back out
in 30 seconds.
- 30-45 seconds,
ah... something.
- You keep talking,
they're gonna take your
handicap placard away.
They're gonna say
you're pretty healthy.
You better be careful.
All right.
Based on the recommendation
of Inspector Quinn,
the matter is dismissed.
♪♪
According to your admission,
it was your party.
- I mean, I guess.
- You just told me,
you co-hosted it.
- Yeah, but it wasn't
just mine.
- Have you ever
been in a court?
- No, first time in my life,
and I am excited
about it.
Thank you very much!
Ordinary tissues left Dakota's
nose sore and red.
So Dad slayed the problem with
Puffs Plus Lotion, instead.
With lotion to soothe and
softness to please.
A nose in need deserves
Puffs, indeed.
♪♪
(Judge Caprio)
- Muammer Tukar.
Good morning, sir,
you are charged with...
- Good morning.
- ... parking overnight.
- Uh, yeah.
First of all, I am sorry
for my English.
Uh...
I am learn-- I am--
I am trying
to learn English.
If I say something wrong,
I am sorry for this.
- You can't say
anything wrong here.
(Muammer)
- Okay.
- Where are you from?
- Turkey.
- How long
have you been here?
- Uh, ten months here.
- You're doing
pretty good.
- Thank you very much.
- Yeah, what do you do?
Are you a student?
- I am-- I am...
studying in-- I am student
in Brown University,
and I am working in labs.
And today...
first time,
I park my car
in 3:00
and after
one and half hour...
when I...
when I come
to near my car,
I found a violation
parking ticket
and there is no sign
about the no parking here
because this is not own.
I just-- I want
to just study in lab two hours
but...
and there is no sign
about no parking
or no overnight parking.
- Okay.
Have you ever been
in a court in Turkey?
- No, first time here.
(Judge Caprio)
- First time in court?
- First time
in my life,
and I am excited about it.
- Well, we hope we give you
a favorable impression
of the United States
judicial system.
All right, so...
let me explain to you
what the situation is, okay?
Everything you said
is accurate.
Everything you said.
There are no signs
that say
you cannot
park overnight, all right?
And, plus, to complicate
matters more,
there's a sign saying
you can park during
certain hours,
and you were not parked
during those certain hours,
so, in your mind,
"I can park here."
Which makes sense to me.
Except that the city
has a...
a set of ordinances.
These are the city laws.
And in here it says
you cannot park overnight
in Providence.
So, before you came
from Turkey,
you were supposed
to read this book.
- Read all of that?
I have just two--
two months here.
(Judge Caprio chuckling)
- So...
it's a very
confusing thing.
People in Providence
know they can't,
but I don't think
it's fair for us
to charge you
for parking overnight,
when, number one,
you didn't know,
number two,
the sign was very misleading.
So that's the short version
of saying
that you won your case.
So when you
get back to Turkey,
you can say, "I was in
the United States,
"and I received
a summons to go to court,
and I fought the system
and I won."
- Am I won now?
(Judge Caprio)
- You win.
- Oh, thank you
very much.
(Judge Caprio chuckling)
Thank you.
- Good luck to you,
the matter is dismissed.
You did a-- you did
a wonderful job.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you again.
- As many of you know,
videos of our cases
have been watched
nearly two billion times
on social media platforms
such as YouTube
and Facebook.
Over half of these views
come from foreign countries.
Almost universally
the viewers comment
that they wished
the court proceedings
in their countries
were as fair
as the ones in our courtroom.
While not always perfect,
the United States
judicial system
is based on the premise
that everyone is innocent
until proven guilty.
That's not
the case everywhere.
I'm pleased that we were
able to demonstrate
that concept in person
to Mr. Tukar
in the hope
that he enjoys
the rest of his stay
in our great country.
Juliana Roland.
- Good morning, Your Honor.
(Judge Caprio)
- Good morning, Juliana.
Juliana, you have
a speeding ticket
on Chalkstone Avenue,
in a school zone.
- Yes.
(Judge Caprio)
- Is there anything
you wanna tell me about?
- Yes, Your Honor.
I'm here from
South Carolina.
I reside in South Carolina.
- In Lexington.
(Juliana)
- And-- I'm sorry.
- In Lexington, South Carolina.
- No, actually,
I'm in Blythewood.
(Judge Caprio)
- Oh--
- It was a rental vehicle.
- Oh.
- I have been
out of the state of Rhode Island
since 1994,
and I was back
visiting my dad--
88 years old.
He was entering
hospice that weekend.
And so...
I'm familiar with
the area.
I lived on Pembroke Avenue
just, you know, north of
Nathanael Greene Middle School.
I'm familiar with the area.
I was staying at a rental
property in Providence
and just picked up speed
going down that hill.
Didn't see the sign
for the school zone.
I know Nathanael Greene School
is there.
I've had one speed ticket
in my driving life, 1991,
on the New York State Thruway.
I had that dismissed
because I was a safe driver.
I just taught my
16-year-old to drive.
She was licensed last week.
So, I'm asking forgiveness,
if not leniency
for this because
I am a safe driver,
and... I'm certainly
guilty of the charge,
but, um...
- Well, you're one mile over
what I would charge ordinarily.
I have...
I have an issue,
not a problem.
I have an issue with that--
the location
of that particular mechanism,
because Chalkstone Avenue
is a hill going down...
- Yes, it is,
yes, it is.
- ... into Raymond Street,
and that's where
they've got the machine.
So you actually would
have to be
pumping the brakes
going down the hill
to be going...
to keep within
the speed limit,
and you were one over
what I usually charge,
so I'm gonna give you
a break.
- Thank you,
thank you, Your Honor.
- Is it your dad that's
going into hospice?
- He passed on June 12th,
so...
last time I saw him
but it was good to be here.
But nice gift.
But thank you for dismissing,
Your Honor.
I appreciate it.
- In memory
of your dad.
- Thank you, thank you--
thanks, Dad.
- Good luck.
You actually had
a pretty good morning.
You know that.
- Both tickets were not me,
and I have to pay
somebody else's mistake.
Yeah, it's a pretty
great morning.
(Judge Caprio)
- I think you better leave
before I change my mind.
Around here, nobody ever does
it.
I Didn't do it.
So when I heard they added Ultra
Oxi
to the cleaning power of Tide,
it was just what we needed.
Dad?
I didn't do it.
#1 stain and odor fighter, #1
trusted.
It's got to be Tide.
Stand up to Chronic
Migraine with BOTOX®.
What if you had fewer headaches
and migraines a month?
BOTOX® prevents
headaches and migraines
before they even start.
BOTOX® is for adults
with Chronic Migraine,
15 or more headache
days a month,
each lasting 4 hours or more.
BOTOX® injections take about
15 mins. in your doctor's office
and are covered
by most insurance.
Effects of BOTOX® may spread
hours to weeks after injection
causing serious symptoms.
Alert your doctor right away,
as difficulty swallowing,
speaking, breathing,
eye problems,
or muscle weakness
can be signs of a
life-threatening condition.
Side effects may
include allergic reactions,
neck and injection site pain,
fatigue, and headache.
Don't receive BOTOX® if
there's a skin infection.
Tell your doctor your
medical history, muscle or
nerve conditions,
and medications,
including botulinum toxins,
as these may increase the
risk of serious side effects.
With the BOTOX® Savings Program,
most people with
commercial insurance
pay nothing out of pocket.
Talk to your doctor and visit
BOTOXChronicMigraine.com
to enroll.
it's time for you to follow
"Caught in Providence"
on Facebook and Instagram.
Stay connected and get access
to show clips
and exclusive digital content.
(Judge Caprio)
- Aga Delgado.
This is a environmental summons.
MC59159.
Charges you with
a noise violation
where there was loud music
coming from your house
at 2:30 in the morning.
- Yeah.
(Judge Caprio)
- Where you having a party?
- Yeah, but this actually--
- What kind of a party
was it?
- This wasn't
actually my house,
so they kind of gave
it to me by accident.
They thought I lived there
because it was
my friend's house,
and I was there at the party
with everybody else,
but they assumed
I lived there,
so they gave me the fine.
The officer had
told me that
I could possibly
fight it or get it dismissed
since I am not a resident
at the house.
- So you were a guest.
- Yeah.
- According to
the police report,
the police spoke to you
and you said that
you were hosting
the welcome-back party.
Is that right?
- No.
Actually, I was
co-hosting with him,
so, yes, I was helping
and I was, like,
a part of it, but--
- So you were the organizer?
- No-- well, it was--
- You were hosting it,
you were the organizer.
- Yeah.
But, I mean, I guess
I really was the one
who took a fall for it.
- Yeah.
So, according to your admission,
it was your party.
- I mean... I guess.
- You just told me,
you co-hosted it.
- Yeah, but it wasn't
just mine.
- Was, uh...
Martin-- was Martin Severs
also--
- Yeah, he also got fined...
(Judge Caprio)
- He got one too.
- ... but his was
dismissed.
- Well, I'm not sure.
I didn't dismiss it.
- Yeah, I know,
I'm just saying.
- Inspector Quinn, you wanna
be heard on this?
- Your Honor,
based on the, uh...
the statements in the report,
um...
- Well, she was
a little disingenuous
when she first-- when she
first came out.
If you had just been honest
when you first came out
and said--
you know, you try
to pull the technical defense.
"Well, I was at my apartment,
I don't live there."
(Aga)
- No.
- You could have easily said,
"I co-hosted the party,
and I told the police
that and that's why I'm here."
- I mean, I was just--
- I know what you were
trying to do.
(Aga)
- Trying to say what
they had told me,
'cause they said that.
- I get it.
Inspector Quinn?
- Your Honor,
based on the report,
it would be $100
or she can have
a trial.
- You would've got
a much better disposition
if you had been honest
from the beginning.
Inspector Quinn
made a recommendation.
$100 fine or come back
and have a trial.
- I mean, I...
- The matter's set down
for trial.
Good luck.
If you wanna be trusted,
you must be honest.
If Ms. Delgado
had simply told me the truth
about her role in the party,
I would have been inclined
to dismiss the charges.
Thomas Jefferson once said,
"Honesty is the first chapter
in the book of wisdom."
It's also the best policy
for every situation
in life.
Including how
you behave in the courtroom.
♪♪
Tony Acevedo.
Tony, you have
three registrations.
- Hmm?
(Judge Caprio)
- Do you understand
what I just said?
- Three registrations?
- Yes.
Now, who's Maria--
- That's my mother,
sir.
(Judge Caprio)
- Valenzuela.
Are you here for her?
- Yes, sir.
- All right, she has
an overnight parking ticket
on Althea...
- Yes, sir.
- There's a $40 penalty.
I waived
the penalty.
- Thank you.
(Judge Caprio)
- So you just saved $40.
You got the first ticket
dismissed.
Now comes the bad news.
You have two
red-light violations.
One goes back
to last year
and one is...
just two weeks ago.
This is a ticket
on North Main and Branch
at 7:38 in the evening.
What's the time on that?
(man)
- .4, Your Honor.
(Judge Caprio)
- All right.
The next one is...
on Pleasant Valley
and Valley Street.
Is that him making
a right-hand turn?
(man)
- Yes, Your Honor.
That's no turn on red
at all.
(Judge Caprio)
- Was this during
the period of construction?
(man)
- Yes, Your Honor.
- I'm gonna find-- I'm gonna
dismiss that ticket
where the signs were confusing,
and it will be
$85 on the other.
This is gonna cost you
a total of $105.
You actually had
a pretty good morning.
You know that.
- Yeah.
Yeah, compared to that both--
both tickets were not me,
and I have to pay
somebody else's mistake.
Yeah, it's a pretty
great morning.
- I think you better leave
before I change my mind.
(man)
- I would.
♪♪
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50-85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
THE THREE WHAT?
THE THREE P'S?
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 54 AND I WAS
A SMOKER BUT QUIT.
ALEX, WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I'M 65, RETIRED,
AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
ALSO $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80
AND I'M ON A FIXED INCOME.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
THAT'S LESS THAN 35 CENTS A DAY.
YOU CANNOT BE TURNED DOWN
BECAUSE OF YOUR HEALTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
OPTIONS START AT $9.95 A MONTH,
PLUS, YOU GET A 30-DAY
MONEY BACK GUARANTEE.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
♪♪
(Judge Caprio)
- Daniel Capella.
- Good morning, Judge.
- Good morning, sir.
All right, you have
a parking meter violation.
- Yeah, it's from my wife.
Maria.
- You're throwing your
wife under the bus already.
- She goes to Providence
Power Yoga there and--
- She goes to yoga?
(Daniel)
- Yeah.
And she had to work
today, so...
- Oh, she's meditating.
- Does yoga,
does all those...
- Yeah, but I mean she must
be meditating now.
She sent you--
she sent you to court.
- I'm gonna have to meditate
for her.
(Judge Caprio)
- All right, what do you
wanna tell me on the merits
of the case?
- There's a parking lot there.
She said she always parks
in the parking lot,
so she doesn't understand.
- This one day she didn't
park in the parking lot
she got the ticket.
- Yeah.
- Now, the ticket
was 25,
you didn't pay it...
so it went
to 75.
But we're gonna
waive the penalties.
- Thank you.
- So you tell your wife
that you took
a really beating today
in front of the judge.
The judge
beat you down.
- I'm hobbling home.
- I don't want
you going home,
telling your wife
you paid $75
and try and get
reimbursed now.
- I wish.
- All right, $25.
- Thank you.
♪♪
UGH, ANOTHER DELAY...
BUT... YOU KEEP BOUNCING
LIKE I'M A BOUNCY CASTLE!
OH YEAH!! 5 STOPS, 0 LEAKS.
WE'RE CRUSHING THIS COMMUTE!
HUGGIES LITTLE MOVERS.
OUR BEST FITTING DIAPER
THAT FITS LIKE A HUGG.
HUGG ON.
Beauty editors have tried
everything.
In search of a whiter smile.
Their choice? Crest
3D Whitestrips.
Our exclusive whitening
formulation
safely whitens 25 times better*.
For a noticeably whiter, smile.
Trust America's #1
whitening treatment.
Crest 3D Whitestrips.
[SFX]
Red Rover, Red Rover
Send Reese's Pieces over
[SFX]
♪
Introducing new
Hershey's Milk Chocolate
and Reese's Pieces
Now in one bar
-Ah, the old crew!
Remember when we all used to go
to the cafeteria
and just chow down midday?
-You mean, like, lunch?
-Come on. Voted
"Most Likely to Help People
Save $668 When They Switch."
-At this school?
-Didn't you get caught
in the laminating machine?
-Ha. [ Sighs ]
-"Box, have a great summer.
Danielle."
Ooh.
Danielle, control yourself.
I'd like to slow it down here
with a special discount
for a special girl.
Danielle, this one's for you.
e a photographecial discount
for a special girl.
that shows this car
was parked right
in front of a sign
that says "tow zone,
no parking."
- He didn't see the sign?
(Judge Caprio)
I'm gonna send him-- I'm gonna
send him for an exam
to check his eyes.
The sign is right
in front of the car.
According to the photograph
I have,
he couldn't open
the door of his car
unless he saw
the sign.
(attendees laughing)
(man)
- Are you kidding?
(Judge Caprio)
- Here's your vehicle,
here's your vehicle,
here's vehicle and-- oh.
Do you still think you
stopped long enough?
- Yes.
Maybe not.
- Waive them.
- Why should I waive this
for your nephew
when you're
telling me that--
- Because he's nowhere
to be found.
- You're telling me
he's totally irresponsible.
On behalf of all the people
of Providence,
thank you for
paying your summons.
- Your record hasn't been
that good, you know?
- I know.
- But you changed.
- The warm-up,
you have this guy here.
- Hey, you trying to take
my brother's job?
- Nah, nah.
Why don't you get
a haircut though?
(laughter)
- I don't have the means.
I only have 75¢ on me.
(announcer)
This is the courtroom
of Judge Frank Caprio,
where people and cases
are met with compassion.
A different kind of judge.
A courtroom
like no other.
This is "Caught in Providence."
- Bertrand Brousseau.
- Morning, Your Honor.
- Morning, sir.
Mr. Brousseau,
you have a, uh,
expired meter ticket
on Angel Street.
- I paid that three times.
- (laughing)
- Three times, and number--
Let me just give you
a little quick rundown.
- All right.
- My daughter works
on top of the bookstore
on Thayer Street.
- Yeah, okay.
- All right, third floor.
Her office is up there.
It was the day before
her birthday.
I went to drop
something off to her.
I-- She was busy.
I know that.
So I just dropped it off.
Took me 30 seconds.
30 seconds to get down
the stairs, up the stairs.
But anyways, um--
- You sure it wasn't
15 seconds?
- I-- It was closer than that.
I'm handicapped.
But, uh, anyways,
the, uh...
the meter had expired.
And I had put eight quarters
in the stupid thing
and it still
didn't go anywhere.
I put a sign on it...
"broken meter."
The lady tagged me anyways.
I went and found her.
I was probably in that office
15 minutes.
I said, you know, what is--
so, anyways.
But they were chasing me
and I kept paying 25, 25, 25.
It never got caught up.
I gave 'em 50 already.
- (chuckling)
- I think--
No, I think I gave 'em 75.
- Thought you gave 50.
- No, some-- well, somebody.
- No, don't fight
with a judge.
- All right, whatever you say.
Anyways, Your Honor--
- All right, well, let me tell--
(laughing)
Let me tell you what happened.
You got the ticket, right?
- Yeah.
- And you paid it.
- But when you paid it,
14 days had expired.
Listen to me.
14 days.
They give you 14 days
to pay the ticket.
- Okay.
- If you don't pay it
in 14 days, it doubles.
So what happened was
the ticket doubled
'cause you didn't pay it
in 14 days,
so you paid $25.
- Right.
- Right?
Then they sent you
a notice saying,
"You owe us another 25
'cause you paid that one late."
Then you didn't pay
that one for 14--
Then you waited 14 days
and you paid that one.
So they took that 25
and they sent you another notice
saying, "You paid
the second 25,
but you didn't do it
within 14 days."
- It's worse than
Bank of America,
you know what I mean?
- You're gonna pay 25
for the rest of your life
every two weeks.
- Right, exactly.
- All right, I'm gonna dis--
I'm gonna dismiss the balance.
- All right.
- Not only that,
I'm gonna give you a credit.
I'm gonna give you a credit
for the extra 25 that you paid.
- All right.
- Because you have
a red light violation.
- There you go.
- This is on Smith and River.
- Right.
- Do you wanna tell me
anything about that?
- Yeah, I'm gonna tell you
about that.
(laughter)
I was on my way--
- It's your daughter again.
I can tell.
- No, listen.
I was on my way to, uh,
say a prayer for you
and for everybody,
to Saint Jude Novena
up on...
on, uh, Chatham Street.
- You prayed for me?
- Yeah, of course.
And, uh... anyways.
The, uh-- I had bad news
from my doctor.
- If he's praying for me,
he's gotta go back,
do a little more.
- Listen, I had bad,
bad news from my doctor.
I was stopped at the red light,
first of all,
and I'm looking at it.
I wasn't texting.
I was just looking
to see what the--
what I had to pick up
and stuff.
And then I see
the light's green,
so-so I put it down,
then all the sudden
it turned red, boom.
52 years I wait my life
to see you.
- (chuckling)
- 52 years.
- You never had a--
- And I'm-- And I'm French.
- You never had
a moving violation?
- Never, never.
Except for that stupid
parking ticket over there.
I thought they were
gonna hang me for that.
- We're gonna take a look at it,
Mr. Brousseau, okay?
We're gonna take--
- Oh, no, I definitely--
I definitely went through it.
- Well, let me take
a look at it.
- Okay, if you want.
(Judge Caprio)
The light is yellow.
It's red.
Boy, you were speeding.
- No, I wasn't.
- Wow.
How fast was he going?
- (man) 34.
- 34?
You were doing
34 miles an hour.
Look at that.
- Maybe I did go through it.
(laughter)
I don't know why
I'm arguing with you.
Anyways.
- Wait a minute.
You just said to me
you were looking down.
- What I thought, yeah.
- You went right through
the light.
- Saint-- Saint Jude
wasn't driving, right?
- No, Saint Christopher,
he jumped out of the car
a long time ago.
- (Quinn) He jumped out?
He saw you were driving,
he jumped out.
(laughter)
- Inspector Quinn,
we have the--
we have the Saint Jude
defense today.
- (Bertrand) Anyway.
- You keep looking.
- I don't know.
Now I can't even see my car.
- Anything else
you wanna tell me?
- Nah, just tell me how much.
(laughter)
- All my friends are Italian.
They all grab my money.
You know what I mean?
- Ohh...
- (chuckling)
- Your Honor,
you're doing a good job.
And these-- the warm-up,
you have this guy here,
I don't know how come
he gets paid but to warm--
warm us up.
- (Quinn) Wow.
(Bertrand)
He's the warm-up.
- Now you're-- Now you're,
uh, buttering me up.
- Yeah, there you go.
I want his job.
Look at all the--
- (Judge Caprio) Oh, yeah, now.
- Look at the electricity
we're paying for.
(laughter)
- Now you're--
It's my brother.
- Ahh, that's why.
- You're trying to take
my brother's job?
- Nah, nah.
Why don't you get
a haircut though?
(Quinn)
Ooh.
(laughter)
- You guys are tough
on all these other people.
Be tough on me.
Arrest me.
- The parking ticket has been--
has been paid.
I'm gonna dismiss that.
- Okay.
- All right.
The red light violation.
It's your first one
in 52 years.
- Yeah.
- You paid $25 extra
for the, uh...
for the parking ticket.
So here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna charge you $35
court costs on the red light,
give you a $25 credit
that you paid
for the parking ticket.
So it's gonna cost you $10.
- For the whole thing?
(laughter)
And hey, give me the 10.
- (Quinn) Your Honor--
- Give me the 10
out of your pocket.
You said it'd be less
than that.
(laughter)
- Good luck.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- (laughing)
- Even though Mr. Brousseau
is French
and Joe is Italian,
they have one thing in common.
They love to bust ba--
excuse me-- bust chops.
- Hey, there you go.
I want his job.
- Now you're-- It's my brother.
- Ahh, that's why.
- You trying to take
my brother's job?
- Nah, nah.
Why don't you get
a haircut though?
(Quinn)
Ooh!
- When's the last time
you had a brain scan?
Kid looks like a movie star--
one that gets killed
in the first act.
- They are definitely brothers
from another mother.
Mr. Brousseau, I have known Joe
for over 20 years,
and trust me, it will take more
than a prayer to Saint Jude
to get the 10 bucks from him.
It will take a miracle.
See, I can bust ba--
excuse me--
chops too.
- I was fired from my job.
- You're in jeopardy now
of having the second car
forfeited to a tow company.
- They asked me
if they could take the car.
I told them no,
so I believe
they did it
without my permission.
With Advil Liqui-Gels,
you'll ask...
What stiff joints?
What bad back?
Advil is... Relief that's
fast. Strength that lasts.
You'll ask...
What pain?
With Advil Liqui-Gels.
Think only specialty stores have
what's new?
Olay has this season's hottest
debut.
Like new Clay Stick Masks.
All Mask, No Mess.
Olay Hydrating Facial Mist.
For hydration on the go.
And our breakthrough Brightening
Eye Cream.
Boosted with Vitamin C.
Get your new beauty fix.
Only by Olay.
- Lisa Pearson.
Lisa, you're charged
with going through a red light
on Service Road 8
and Broadway...
on July 15th.
Let's take a look at this.
Light is yellow.
It's red.
And you almost made it.
(man)
Red, Your Honor, now.
Here's her vehicle.
(Judge Caprio)
See where your vehicle is?
And the light just turned red.
- First of all,
I'd like to let you know
that I'm on disability.
Second of all,
I had my niece
and my nephew over,
and I believe they took my car
because I haven't had
any violations on my license
in at least five
to seven years.
So they asked me
if they could take the car.
I told them no,
so I believe they did it
without my permission.
And I believe
that he's the one
'cause I don't recall
going through no red light.
- This was at, uh, like,
5:00 in the evening.
Would that be you?
- Yeah, I-- no.
I don't believe it was me.
I believe the kids took the car.
I call them kids
'cause they're younger than me.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- But, uh...
But, uh...
- You also have a ticket
for parking
in a loading zone
on Union Street.
I'm gonna dismiss
the loading zone ticket.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- But when your name came up,
they picked put his old ticket.
I'm gonna dismiss it.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- All right, now we have
to get back to the big--
big guns here.
This red light violation, okay?
I believe you, all right?
But here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna charge you $35
court costs,
and get it from them.
You hear me?
- Yes.
- 'Cause you are responsible
if someone who drives your car--
- Your Honor,
I can't afford it really
because I'm on disability.
And I only have,
uh, 75¢ on me
until my check comes the 1st.
I don't have any money.
And then I--
I bought my car,
and, uh, I--
- Lisa, Lisa, Lisa, Lisa.
I--
I'm dismissing it.
- Oh, God bless you.
Thank you, Your Honor.
- And good luck.
- I really, really appreciate
letting me be able
to not have to pay the fine
because I...
I don't have the means.
- All right, it's okay.
- I'm struggling.
And I'm trying to get
my condition together
with my disability, so...
- (Judge Caprio) Good luck.
- ...I'm trying my best.
(Judge Caprio)
Good luck to you.
- Thank you so much again.
- Bye-bye.
- Have a great day.
♪♪
- Patricia Lovely.
- Morning.
- Morning, Patricia.
You have two
red light violations
and three parking tickets.
- I thought
I was coming in
because I hadn't gotten a ticket
in so long
and I was going to talk to you
about the good driver thing,
and then--
- Yeah.
- I-- then--
- You got two red lights.
- I know.
- I'm gonna dismiss one.
- Okay, thank you so much.
- All right,
now what do you want
to tell me about
the parking tickets?
- Just that, you know, I-I--
It was right when they started
doing that thing where they--
you had a parking spot
and you had pay
down the street somewhere,
and I had no idea
how to do that.
- Oh, the multi-spacace meter.
- Yeah.
But I did do it, and I know that
that was this--
it was back then
when they started doing that
and I didn't know anything
about all that.
- Well, they got 'em
at three different locations.
It's not one location.
- I know, I know.
No, I know.
I'm bad-- it's my bad.
I'm just really happy to--
I wanna clear my slate.
- Are you ready to confess?
- I am.
I feel like this is confession.
- Inspector Quinn,
we have a confession.
- (laughing)
Your Honor, it's been a while
since I've been to confession,
so, uh...
- (Judge Caprio) Oh.
(Quinn)
...I can't fault the motorist.
- Well, while you're confessing,
we have a number
of unsolved crimes upstairs.
Do you wanna confess
to any of those?
We could clear them all out.
- Okay.
- What do you think,
Inspector Quinn?
- That-- I will accept
that confession,
Your Honor, all day long,
to clear the desk.
- All right, I'm gonna fine you
$85 for one of the red lights
and $30 for one
of the parking tickets.
- I appreciate that.
- So it's gonna cost you $115.
- Okay, thank you
very, very much, sir.
- Good luck to you.
- Okay.
- I know you can't be
his girlfriend
because basketball
is his girlfriend.
If I was standing next to you,
I wouldn't wear that T-shirt.
- Thank you.
- Donna Morales.
Good morning, Donna.
- Good morning.
- Donna, your car
was, uh... towed.
It was booted first.
It wasn't paid.
As a result, it got towed.
- Correct.
- The car got towed...
last month?
- Yes.
- Why did it take you a month
to come in here on this?
- Well, Your Honor,
I just, uh--
I was fired from my job.
I didn't have a job.
Um--
- No.
Well, let me go through this.
Your car was booted...
two months ago?
- No, that's, um, the Nissan.
I have my Infinity
that was just booted last week.
- Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
There are two vehicles here?
- Yes, two vehicles, but--
- Let me go through this slowly.
(chuckles)
The first vehicle is a Nissan.
I'm just-- I just know
what I have before me.
- Correct.
- It appears that that car
was blooted-- booted
a couple of months ago.
- Correct.
- And then towed.
- It's still at the tow company?
- Correct.
- Are you here
for that vehicle?
- No, I'm not.
Unfortunately, I--
The reason why it got towed
and I didn't come in--
I was not able to register.
I was in the process
of registering.
I bought it from a dealer
off of the Internet.
And something was wrong
with the title that--
so it looked like
three people were on there.
I was dealing with Miss Mancini
from the DMV.
She said, unfortunately,
we couldn't get it registered.
- Oh, you bought a car.
To use--
To use the street language,
the car was a gaffe, right?
- Basically, yes.
And--
- So, all right.
They had trouble with the title.
You bought it online.
You couldn't get it cleared.
All right,
I understand all that.
So you forfeited that car.
- Right.
- The tow guys got it, right?
- Right, so that's why I didn't.
- So you said, "Keep it.
I don't care about it."
- 'Cause you can't-- the DMV
said I can't register it.
- And... on the Infinity,
you had 11 tickets.
None of which were paid.
Most of them were
overnight parking
outside your house.
- Yes, Your Honor.
My landlord, uh--
I tried to file for the, um--
to see if I can get
the overnight parking ticket,
but because we--
there's six apartments
in my house,
the landlord had to go down
and do something, they said.
He finally just did it now.
And I lost my job.
That's why I didn't come in.
I'm just back to work,
so now I can take care
of the parking tickets
and everything.
I'm not here to give you
an excuse.
I'm fully responsible for it
and willing to pay.
- All right, Donna,
you're in jeopardy now
of having the second car towed
and forfeited to a tow company.
- Correct.
- So what do you wanna tell me
about these?
Did you come
prepared today to--
prepared to pay-- to pay
for the boot to be released?
- I have right now $300,
Your Honor, that I can give,
and then I could come back
every week
and make a payment
towards them tickets--
- Your record hasn't been
that good.
You know that?
- I know, I know.
- But you changed.
- I-I have a good job.
I lost my job.
I got a-- I'm back to work.
I am not losing--
I'm not gonna lose my job.
I have no other choice.
But...
(laughing)
But I will be making
the payments, Your Honor.
- In your defense...
In your defense...
'cause I really wanna be fair
with you, okay?
Almost all of these tickets
are parking in front
of your house overnight.
And I have some sympathy for you
because of that.
'Cause we have an ordinance
in Providence
that you cannot park overnight
on the streets in Providence.
And I know that many--
many landlords
don't have sufficient number
of parking spaces
for their tenants
and the tenants have no choice
but to park on the street.
All right, the original tickets
are $835.
The original tickets.
All right, I'm gonna dismiss
a number of the tickets
on Monticello Street.
It's gonna cost you
a $100 boot fee,
$300 for the tickets,
and I'm gonna release the boot
as soon as you pay the 300,
which will be today, okay?
- Okay.
- You have a $100 balance.
You're gonna have
a $100 balance.
- Okay.
- Try to pay that
as quick as possible
so that you can buy
a parking pass
so you can park the car in front
of your house for a year.
Okay, so as soon as you pay
the other 100,
you'll be eligible
to buy a parking pass.
- Okay, I can pay that
next Friday, Your Honor.
Thank you so much.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- I'm trying to help you
to help yourself,
so, please, help yourself.
- I definitely will.
I definitely will be here Friday
to pay that $100.
- Okay, good luck to you.
- Thank you so much.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- Rayelle Fernandez.
This is a parking ticket
on Benevolent Street.
- Yes, I never received it.
I just received the paper
in the mail,
so we came in today
to take care of it.
- All right.
So you're looking to waive
the penalties.
- Yes, sir.
- Yes.
- All right.
Who was driving the car?
- He was.
- (Judge Caprio) You?
- Yes, sir.
I was at work.
I work for a moving company.
- Now who's this?
- This is Rayelle.
- I'm the owner of the car.
- Are you friendly?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
(man)
I work for a moving company.
- I know you can't be
his girlfriend
because basketball
is his girlfriend.
(laughter)
- No.
- I mean, I'm not sure--
I don't want to get involved
here in any personal matters,
all right?
- No, I coach basketball, sir.
- Well...
- I coach.
- You know, just in case
she was disillusioned,
thinking that she had
a chance here, right?
His girlfriend
is basketball, so--
And he's proud of it.
See, so, I don't know.
If I was standing next to you,
I wouldn't wear that T-shirt.
- Thank you.
(laughter)
- Well, I think you should
discuss this after you leave.
If you need a mediator,
I'll mediate it, okay?
- (Rayelle) Okay.
- All right.
But I'm gonna waive
the penalties.
- Thank you.
- So she did a good job
talking for you.
I'd change that shirt.
(chuckling)
All right, it's $20.
- Thank you.
- Thanks a lot, Your Honor.
- Have a good day.
♪♪
You want a fresh-smelling home,
but some air fresheners use
heavy, overwhelming scents.
Introducing Febreze ONE;
a new range
of innovative air fresheners
with no heavy perfumes
that you can feel good about
using in your home
to deliver a light,
natural-smelling freshness.
Febreze ONE
neutralizes stale, stuffy odors
and releases a
subtle hint of fragrance
like Bamboo
or Lemongrass Ginger.
To eliminate odors
with no heavy perfumes,
try new Febreze ONE.
Brand Power.
Helping you buy better.
UGH... WHAT THE WHAT?
OKAY WIPE, PRETTY-PLEASE
DO YOUR THING.
NICE! NAILED IT!
HUGGIES® NATURAL CARE® WIPES,
GENTLE LIKE A HUG.
HUGG ON.
- I'll take the 50.
(laughing)
I'll take the $50.
- You plead the 50?
Used to be the 5th.
She pleads the 50.
(laughter)
- Um, yeah, that'd be--
I'll be fine with that.
You've explained I was,
you know--
- You wanna negotiate $49.50?
- (laughing) No, no, no.
- You wanna pay the full 50?
- Yes, I'll go for it.
- Okay.
(Judge Caprio)
Are you kidding?
♪ ♪ ♪
IF YOU HAVE RECURRING
CONSTIPATION AND BELLY PAIN,
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR AND
SAY YESSS! TO LINZESS.
YESSS!
LINZESS TREATS ADULTS WITH IBS
WITH CONSTIPATION
OR CHRONIC CONSTIPATION.
LINZESS CAN HELP RELIEVE
YOUR BELLY PAIN,
AND LETS YOU HAVE MORE FREQUENT
AND COMPLETE BOWEL MOVEMENTS.
SEE IF YOU'RE ELIGIBLE
TO GET 90 DAYS
FOR AS LITTLE AS 30 DOLLARS.
DO NOT GIVE LINZESS TO
CHILDREN LESS THAN 6,
AND IT SHOULD NOT BE GIVEN TO
CHILDREN 6 TO LESS THAN 18,
IT MAY HARM THEM.
DO NOT TAKE LINZESS IF YOU
HAVE A BOWEL BLOCKAGE.
GET IMMEDIATE HELP
IF YOU DEVELOP UNUSUAL
OR SEVERE STOMACH PAIN,
ESPECIALLY WITH BLOODY
OR BLACK STOOLS.
THE MOST COMMON SIDE EFFECT
IS DIARRHEA, SOMETIMES SEVERE.
IF IT'S SEVERE,
STOP TAKING LINZESS
AND CALL YOUR
DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
GAS, STOMACH-AREA
PAIN, AND SWELLING.
SO SAY YESSS!
TO HELP FOR RECURRING
CONSTIPATION.
YESSS! TO HELP
FOR BELLY PAIN.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
AND SAY YESSS! LINZESS.
- I was set up.
The guy who was crossing
was an undercover cop.
- Undercover cops,
they-- they count as
human beings, too.
- I witnessed something
that I thought was
both racist
and classist.
- I took one of the plates
from my old car
and put it
on the new car.
- You put it on two cars?
- Yeah.
- You convicted yourself now.
(announcer)
This is the courtroom
>>> THIS IS "DAILY BLAST LIVE."
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>> EVERYBODY IS TALKING ABOUT
THIS.
>> ALWAYS LIVE, ALWAYS REAL,
ALWAYS UNPREDICTABLE.
>> YOU ARE TOTALLY OFF BASE
HERE.
>> LOG ON AND JOIN OUR LIVE
CONVERSATION.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M SAYING
THIS.
I DO AGREE WITH YOU.
>> "DBL" STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> THREE, TWO --
>> WELCOME TO "DBL."
IT'S WEDNESDAY, FEBRUARY 13th.
WE ARE LIVE AND WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT.
I'M HERE WITH TORY, AL, JEFF
AND I'M SAM.
WE HAVE DR. DREW.
YOU'RE NOT ONLY A FRIEND BUT MY
MENTOR.
>> THERE'S A REASON WE WORK
WITH YOU.
YOU'RE GOOD.
>> THAT MEANS SO MUCH TO ME.
>> EMERGENCY FALLOUT.
>> THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE,
DR. DREW.
WE BEGIN WITH A STORY WE'VE
BEEN TRACKING.
HE JUSSIE'S REPS SAID CHICAGO
PD FIND HIS STORY CONSISTENT AND
CREDIBLE.
THIS COME HAS DAY AFTER A
SPOKESPERSON SAID THE KNOWN
RECORDS DO NOT MEET THE BURDEN
FOR A CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION
HAS THEY WERE LIMITED AND
HEAVILY REACTED.
JUSSIE'S REPS CLAIM INFORMATION
WAS REMOVED TO PROVENT OTHERS
WHO HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THE
ATTACK.
CHECK OUT THIS TEASER.
>> AT ANY POINT DURING THE
ATTACK DID YOU FEAR FOR YOUR
ATTACK?
>> YOU HAVE BEEN FOLLOWING IT.
WHAT WOULD YOU SAY ABOUT THE
NARRATIVE?
>> IT'S NOT OUR JOB TO CREATE A
NARRATIVE.
IF HE HAS OVERSTATED IT, I'M
STILL WORRIED.
SO ALL OF US SIT BACK.
IT'S NOT OUR BUSINESS.
>> TORY, YOU HAVE A STRONG
TAKE.
>> INNOCENT UNTIL PROVEN
GUILTY.
IF IT'S NOT TRUE, DR. DREW IS
RIGHT, THERE MAY BE SOMETHING
ELSE WRONG.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN ANYTHING.
I MEAN TOM BRADY DIDN'T GIVE UP
HIS PHONE WHEN IT'S DEFLATE-
GATE AND WE'RE JUMPING ON THIS
GUY.
>> ANYTHING WE GET FROM THE
STORY WILL PUSH THE NARRATIVE.
THERE'S MONEY TO BE MADE FROM
DIVISION.
UNFORTUNATELY, IT'S THE WORLD
WE LIVE IN.
THE CONSPIRACY THEORISTS SAY
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE IS A HOAX,
PARKLAND, SANDY HOOK, PIZZA
GATE.
EVERYBODY, UNFORTUNATELY HAS A
FINANCIAL INTEREST.
I GUARANTEE A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE
NOT FANS OF HIS AND DO CARE
ABOUT HIS PHYSICAL WELL-BEING.
THEY JUST SEE THE KID AS A WAY
IT FURTHER THEIR AGENDA.
>> I WOULD ENCOURAGE PEOPLE IF
YOU THINK THERE ARE HOLES IN
HIS STORY, WHICH I DON'T, WAIT
FOR THE INTERVIEW.
>> WE WILL BE COVERING THE
INTERVIEW TOMORROW.
>> THE MEDIA CREATES NARRATIVE.
THOSE HEADLINES, THAT'S FOR THE
GOOD OF THE NARRATIVE.
THEY WANT IT MAKE MONEY.
>> BE AN INDIVIDUAL THINKER AND
CHIME IN "DBL" NATION.
WE FINALLY HAVE GOOD NEWS
COMING OUT OF WASHINGTON, D.C.
MANY.
>>WE ARE TWO DAYS AWAY FROM A
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
CONGRESSIONAL LEADERS CAME UP
WITH A TENTATIVE DEAL.
SOURCES SAY HE IS EXPECTED TO
SIGN IT.
IN THE MEANTIME TED CRUZ IS
BACKING ANOTHER PLAN.
CRUZ SAID WE SHOULD USE THE
MONEY U.S. PROSECUTORS ARE
SEEKING FROM NOW CONVICTED EL
CHAPO.
THEY'RE SEEKING $14 BILLION IN
PROFLTS AND CRUZ SAID THAT
MONEY SHOULD GO TOWARD SECURITY
BORDER.
>>> WELL, WE HAVE A NEW TO DOG.
MEET KING THE FOX TERRIER.
I CALLED IT THE BEST IN SHOW
LAMPS NIGHT AT THE WESTMINSTER
DOG SHOW.
COMPETITION WAS ROUGH.
THE FOX TERRIER WON THE TOP
PRIZE.
THIS MARKS THE 15th TIME THAT
BREED HAS COME OUT ON TOP.
THE LONG HAIRED DACHSHUND DID
NOT WIN.
AND THE SKIPPER WHO WON THE
NONSPORTING GROUP WAS
DISQUALIFIED.
>> SCANDAL.
>> DUE TO A CONFLICT OF
INTEREST.
>> I THOUGHT I WAS BACK IN
FRANCE.
>> AND THIS SUSSEX SPANIEL
NAMED BEAN WHO WON THE SPORTING
GROUP AND MEET WILMA THE BOXER,
BUT IT WASN'T JUST US HUMANS.
CHECK OUT ALL THESE DOGS WHO
REALLY GOT INTO THE ACTION.
TORY, I KNOW, FIRST OF ALL,
SCANDAL.
>> BIG SCANDAL.
>> SKIPPER KEY WAS IN IT.
THEY SHOOK HANDS WITH THE JUDGE
AND SAID I NEED YOU TO LEAVE.
THAT IS SCANDAL, AM I RIGHT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> BECAUSE THE JUDGE WAS A CO-
OWNER OF SAID DOG.
>> SHOULDN'T THAT BE ILL LOCAL?
>> THIS WAS.
HE DID A NICE LAUGH AND WALKED.
>> THE BEARDED GUY THAT LOOKS
LIKE SHERLOCKS, HE LOOKS LIKE A
DOG.
AT SOME POINT THAT DOG WAS ON.
HE STOOD LIKE THIS AND HE, THE
CROWD.
>> CAN I GET A ONE IS THE ON
TORY WHEN SHE DOES THAT.
THIS IS THE DACHSHUND, ONE SHOT
ON TORY.
>> PLEASE DON'T PUT ME IN IT.
>> IT WAS MADISON SQUARE
GARDEN, THANK YOU.
>> LOOK AT JEFF.
>> WE COVERED THIS STORY MORE
THAN THE SUPER BOWL.
>> CAN ANYONE EXPLAIN WHY I
WATCH IT EVERY YEAR AFTER THE
MACY'S THANKSGIVING DAY PARADE.
>> THEY SHOULD HAVE RESCUE DOGS
ONLY.
>> THEY CALL IT THE ONE PEOPLE
DON'T WASH EYE LIKE THE
BEAUTIFUL DOGS.
COME ON.
IT DOESN'T MOON YOU HAVE TO BUY
ONE.
>> COMING UP ON "DBL," DR. DREW
ANSWERS YOUR BURNING QUESTIONS
ABOUT LOVE AND RELATIONSHIP AND
WHY YOU SHOULDN'T MESS WITH
SINGER MIRANDA LAMBERT.
PLUS, ACTOR ANSON WILSON TELLS
US ABOUT HAPPY DAYS AND'S
SQUIRE MAGAZINE IS IN THE
CENTER OF A FIRE STORM OVER
THIS COVER.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHY A LITTLE
LATER.
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "DBL."
I WOULD HAVE A SPECIAL GUEST.
YOU KNOW HIM FROM LOVE LINE AND
CELEBRITY -- IT'S DR. DREW
PINSKY.
THIS IS IMPORTANT.
A LOT OF OUR VIEWERS AT HOME,
YOU LOVE HIS ADVICE ON
ADDICTION AND RELATIONSHIPS BUT
TODAY WE'RE FOCUSING ON
RELATIONSHIPS AND ASKED VIEWERS
TO SEND IN FOR A SEGMENT WE'RE
CALLING DEAR DR. DREW DBL.
>> ONE PERSON MY BEDROOM LIFE
WITH MY GIRLFRIEND  SUCKS.
THREE TIME AS WEEK IF I'M
LUCKY.
>> THREE TIMES A WEEK ABOVE
AVERAGE BY THE WAY.
>> THAT'S ABOVE AVERAGE?
YES.
>> AVERAGE IN A LONG TERM
RELATIONSHIP.
>> WHAT ABOUT A NEW
>> SOME PEOPLE ARE AT THAT
RATE.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
PEOPLE HAVE TO REACH A
COMPROMISE.
>> MORNING AND NIGHT, JEFF.
>> I LOVE SLEEP.
>> IT'S ABOUT COMPROMISING.
YOU HAVE TO TELL HER THIS IS
NOT YOUR RATE AND YOU HAVE TO
STEP IT UP.
ONE OF THE THINGS I SEE
COMMONLY IN YOUNG COUPLES WHEN
A FEMALE SEXUAL DESIRE DOES NOT
MATCH A MAN SHE MAY BE ON A
HIGH PROJEST TER PRONE BIRTH
CONTROL.
SO TAKE A LOOK AT THE BIRTH
THE PROGESTERONE.
>> THIS GUY.
HE'S LIKE A FOUNTAIN OF
KNOWLEDGE.
>> ELLIE SAYS MY HUSBAND
GAMBLES COMPULSIVELY AND
FREQUENTS GENTLEMEN'S CLUBS.
WE ARE DROWNING IN DEBT.
SHOULD I WALK OUT.
>> ELLIE MAE, LIKE FROM THE
BEVERLY HILLBILLIES?
THIS IS A TRAGEDY AND THIS IS A
GREAT EXAMPLE OF HOW REAL
GAMBLING ADDICTION DESTROYS
LIFE.
THERE COULD BE SEXUAL
ADDICTION.
GO TO AL-ANON.
THERE'S SPECIFIC ONES FOR
GAMBLING AND SEX ACTS BUT AL-
ANONIS EASY TO FIND.
HE GETS TREATMENT OR YOU LEAVE.
>> ANOTHER WE BOTH PEOPLE
STRONGLY.
SHE'S NOT READY FOR A
RELATIONSHIP.
WE CAN'T STOP SEEING EACH
OTHER.
IT FEELS LIKE A REBOUND.
>> I HAVE TO FINISH, DOES HE GO
TO GA, GAMBLING'S ANONYMOUS.
OR SEX ACTS AEN IN ANONYMOUS.
WHEN SOMEONE IS GOING THROUGH A
DIVORCE YOU'RE MORE OF A LIFE
PRESERVER WHEN SOMEONE'S GOING
THROUGH A HORRIBLE CRISIS.
I WOULD NEED A WHOLE LOT MORE
INFORMATION.
>> COULD IT WORK OUT?
>> I COULD BUT I HAVE BAD
FEELINGS ABOUT THIS.
>> INTERESTING.
>> I JUST READ RUTH.
>> TREVOR IN TAMPA SAID MY
GIRLFRIEND GETS MAD AT ME FOR
NOT POSTING PICTURES OF US ON
SOCIAL MEDIA.
I LIKE TO POST ABOUT MY
HOBBIES, SHE THINKS I'M HIDING
SOMETHING.
>> THAT'S A RELATABLE ONE.
>> YOU, SIR NEED TO STEP UP
BECAUSE SHE'S LETTING YOU KNOW
SOMETHING SIMPLE THAT COULD
MAKE YOU VERY HAPPY.
WHY WOULDN'T YOU IF IT WOULD
MAKE HER FEEL GOOD.
IF SHE'S SOMEONE YOU LOVE, WHY
WOULDN'T YOU DO THAT.
>> WHAT'S WRONG WITH OUR
DYSFUNCTION HALL FAMILY?
>> I'M MOSTLY WORRIED ABOUT YOU
AND SAM, JEFF.
>> WE HEARD A LITTLE BIT ABOVE
NORMAL IN CERTAIN AREAS.
I GET THAT A LOT.
FIVE MINUTES AGO.
>> COMING UP ON "DBL," A LOT OF
PEOPLE ARE SAYING ESQUIRE
MAGAZINE MISSED THE MARK WITH
THIS COVER AND ANSON WILLIAMS
FROM "HAPPY DAYS" SETTLES THE
SCORE.
WHO'S COOLER POTSY OR THE FONZ?
>>> TODAY'S WATCH AND WIN WORD
IS SUNGLASSES.
>> WELCOME BACK TO "DBL."
ALL MONTH LONG I'M TALKING WITH
TV LEGENDS FROM THE PAST TO
FIND OUT WHERE THEY ARE NOW.
SO I HEADED TO THE HOLLYWOOD
MUSEUM IN THE HEART OF LOS
ANGELES, CALIFORNIA AND SAT
DOWN WITH ANSON WILLIAMS,
BETTER KNOWN AS POTSIE FROM
MONDAY, TUESDAY, HAPPY DAYS.
CHECK THIS OUT.
MONDAY, TUESDAY, I'M IN HEAVEN.
IT WAS A VERY GOOD OPENING.
I'M HERE WITH SOMEONE I'VE
ALWAYS HAD A CRUSH ON.
IT'S ANSON WILLIAMS.
>> THOSE ARE ORIGINAL LYRICS.
I'VE NEVER HEARD THOSE BEFORE.
>> YOU PLAYED ONE OF THE MOST
ICONIC CHARACTERS ON TV.
DO YOU HAVE A FAVORITE MEMORY?
>> THE BEST MEMORY, WE A
SOFTBALL TEAM AND WE WENT ALL
AROUND THE WORLD.
>> WHAT WAS YOUR TEAM NAME?
>> LET ME GUESS, HAPPY DAYS.
>> SO YOU WERE BEST FRIENDS
WITH RICKY CUNNINGHAM, RON
HOWARD, WHICH ONE MADE YOU
LAUGH MORE.
>> LOOK AT THE CHARACTER
FONZIE.
>> DO YOU STILL KEEP IN TOUCH?
>> WE DO.
WE'VE BEEN FRIENDS FOREVER.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE HAD CRASH ON
YOU BUT EVER WANTED TO BE
FONZIE?
>>  WHO WOULDN'T WANT TO BE
FONZIE.
I LIKE POTSIE BETTER.
>> I HEARD ONE OF THE BEATLES
CAME BY.
>> YOU'RE ON A SET, HAPPY.
THERE'S A GUY STANDING BY THE
COFFEE MACHINE LOOKS LIKE JOHN
LENNON.
OH, YEAH, JOHN LENNON CAME HERE
TO HANG OUT WITH US.
YOU BET.
IT WAS JOHN LENNON COMING TO
HANG OUT WITH US.
WE'RE PROFESSIONALS.
WE DON'T ASK FOR ANYBODY.
, ON THIS SHOW IT WOULD BE THE
FIRST.
A VERY NICE LOOKING MAN.
EXCUSE ME, I DON'T MEAN TO
INTERRUPT.
IT'S JULIAN LENNON.
40 YEARS LATER.
CAN WE TAKE A SELFIE.
>> THAT'S A GREAT STORY.
YOU FOUND A WAY TO CURE RATE IT
IN ONE AREA.
IT'S THE BEST.
>> THANK YOU, ANSON WILLIAMSS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SUBSCRIBE TO OUR YOUTUBE
CHANNEL TO CHECK OUT AN
EXTENDED INTERVIEW.
IT'S A SIMPLE SOLUTION TO
COMBAT DROWSY DRIVING AND IT
CLAN SAVE LIVES.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "DBL."
WHETHER YOU'RE MORE OF A DATE
NIGHT OR THE GIFT GIVING TYPE
ON VALENTINE'S DAY, MY GIRL
TORY HAVE SOME TIPS.
YOU KNOW WHO IT IS.
IT'S PRESENTED BY CAR SHIELD.
TORY, WHAT'S A PERFECT VALENTINE
VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> AT THE END OF THE DAY I'M
WRITING A COUPON FOR A HUG.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> I THINK VALENTINE'S DAY IS
EMBARRASSING.
I GOT A PIZZA BUT I CUT IT IN
THE SHAPE OF A HEART.
>> WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
>> I DON'T LIKE ROSE PETALS
LEADING TO THE BEDROOM WITH THE
CEILING FAN.
IT'S THE SAME BEDROOM.
YOU JUST STRAIGHTENED OUT THE
COMFORTABLE.
>> TO AVOID LAST-MINUTE HASSLE
WE HAVE SUGGESTIONS.
DISCUSS EXPECTATIONS WITH YOUR
PARTNER.
ENJOY THE GIFT WITH CAR SHIELD.
THEY PROTECT ITS MEMBERS CALL 1-
800-505-9619 FOR A FREE QUOTE.
>> WELL, YOU AND AL ALWAYS HAVE
SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT IN
THOSE CARS.
>> I LIKE THAT YOU AGREE THAT
ROMANCE IS EMBARRASSING.
>> I THINK IT'S SEXY.
>> HE'S SAYING TO WATCH IT.
>> WEIRD TO SEE.
>> WILL HAVE A PHONE CALL WITH
SUSANNE.
IF YOU'RE LEAVING US YOU CAN
WATCH US ON FACEBOOK.
>> A COVER STORY EXPLODES WHEN
ESQUIRE HIGH LIGHTS A CAUCASIAN
TEEN DURING BLACK HISTORY
MONTH.
DID THEY MISS THE MARK OR IS IT
MUCH TO DO ABOUT NOTHING.
PLUS, FOOD FIGHT.
WHY COUNTRY STAR MIRANDA
LAMBERT DUMPED A PERFECTLY GOOD
SALAD INTO A LADY'S LAP.
DID SOMEONE CALL THE DOCTOR?
THIS PRESIDENTS DAY,
HAVERTYS IS HONORING
PRESIDENT MOM.
SHE MADE THE EXECUTIVE DECISION
TO BUY STORE BOUGHT COOKIES
FOR THE BAKE SALE.
SHE PARDONED EMMA FOR...
BEING EMMA.
AND THEN THERE WAS THE WHOLE
CONE CRISIS THING.
PRESIDENT MOM, THIS PRESIDENTS
DAY SALE IS FOR YOU!
EVERYTHING IS ON SALE.
GET BIG SAVINGS ON SOFAS, BEDS,
DINING SETS AND MORE.
NOW THAT'S FISCALLY RESPONSIBLE
LEADERSHIP.
HAVERTYS.
Life Looks Good.
FO
>>> THIS IS "DAILY BLAST LIVE".
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT WHAT YEAR
TALKING ABOUT.
>> BECAUSE EVERYONE IS TALKING
ABOUT THIS.
>> ALWAYS LIVE, ALWAYS REAL,
ALWAYS UNPREDICTABLE.
>> YOU'RE TOTALLY OFF BASE
HERE.
>> LOG ON AND JOIN OUR LIVE
CONVERSATION.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M SAYING
THIS.
I DO AGREE WITH YOU.
>> DBL STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> 3,2,...
>>> WELCOME TO DBL.
IT IS FRIDAY, FEBRUARY 8th,
2019.
YES, WE ARE LIVE AND WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
I'M HERE WITH TORY, JEFF, AL
AND I'M SAM.
LET'S GET STARTED.
THE RICHEST MAN IN THE WORD
SAYS HE IS BEING EXTORTED AND
EXTORTED AND BLACKMAILED.
JEFF SAYS THE COMPANY IS TRYING
TO EXTORT HIM WITH EXPLICIT
PHOTOS.
THIS ALL STEMMED FROM THE
NATIONAL ENQUIRER STORY ABOUT
HIS AFFAIR WHICH INCLUDED
PRIVATE TEXTS BETWEEN THE TWO.
HE HIRED AN INVESTIGATORS TO
FIND OUT HOW THEY GOT THOSE
TEXTS BUT NOW HE CLAIMS A.M.
I THROUGH A LAWYER TRIED  TO
GET HIM TO HOLD OFF ON HIS
INVESTIGATION OR ELSE THEY
WOULD PUBLISH THE PHOTOS WHICH
INCLUDES A QUOTE BELOW THE
BELT.
THERE IS A POTENTIAL POLITICAL
ANGLE TO THE STORY AS HE OWNS
THE WASHINGTON POST WHICH HAS
BEEN VERY CRITICAL OF THE
PRESIDENT.
MEANWHILE AMI HAS A PLEA
AGREEMENT OVER THE HUSH MONEY
PAYMENTS DURING THE 2016
PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN THAT MAY
HAVE BENEFITED DONALD TRUMP.
THEY SAID IT ACTED LAWFULLY AND
WILL INVESTIGATE THE CLAIMS.
TORY, YOU'RE OUR LEGAL EAGLE.
ANYTHING READING THOSE E-MAILS
SAY IT IS BLACKMAIL EXTORTION
ONE OR ONE.
>> THE FIRST THING YOU HAVE
HAVE TO KNOW THEY WILL TRY TO
GET OUT OF IT.
IT IS BLACKMAIL.
YOU SHOULD NEVER WRITE THIS
DOWN IN E-MAIL BECAUSE IT IS
HORRIBLE, BUT HAVING THAT E-
MAIL IS PROOF OF EVERYTHING.
I THINK JEFF BEZOS HAS NOTHING
TO LOSE HERE.
HIS REPUTATION MAY HAVE GONE
DONE, BUT I SEE PEOPLE ARE
APPLAUDING HIM AND SAYING, HIS
FAMOUS QUOTE IS I THINK I'LL
ROLL THE LOG OVER AND SEE WHAT
CRAWLS OUT.
>> THIS IS WORRY SOME BECAUSE
NOT EVERYONE HAS THE RESOURCES
THAT HE HAS AND IF YOU DO, WHAT
IF MY CHILDREN SEE THIS?
WHAT IF MY BOARD OF DIRECTORS
ARS UPSET BAY THIS.
YOU SEE A COMPANY THAT IS ABOVE
THE LAW.
WITH THAT TYPE OF POWER WHAT
HAVE THEY DONE BEFORE THAT WE
DON'T KNOW ABOUT?
>> WE HAVE THE CATCH AND KILL
STORY THAT WE TALKED ABOUT IN
PREVIOUS SHOWS.
AT THIS POINT, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHY EXTORTION AND
BLACKMAIL ARE NOT TREATED LIKE
THE CRIMES THEY ARE.
THIS IS ILLEGAL.
A LOT OF PEOPLE DON'T HAVE THE
RESOURCES THAT ARE BLACKMAILED
FOR YEARS.
MARIAH CAREY.
SHE IS A PERSON OVEN NOR MUS
MEANS.
WE KEEP SLAPPING PEOPLE ON THE
WRISTS AND YOU GET SIX MONTHS
OF PROBATION.
UNTIL THEY ARE TREATED LIKE
THEY ARE TRUE CRIMES THEY ARE
OR CORRUPTION, I DON'T THINK
WE'LL SEE A CHANGE IN THIS
BEHAVIOR.
>>> ANOTHER SMEAR CAMPAIGN THE
ENQUIRER DID.
CHECK THIS OUT.
>>
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THEY PUT THAT SHE HATES MY
GRAY HAIR.
SHE NEVER REPORTED THAT.
>> THAT IS YOUR SIGNATURE.
LOOK.
>> WHAT IS UP WITH THAT?
>> I KNOW.
>> NOW I'M REALLY DONE WITH THE
INQUIRER.
>> HOW DID THEY GET YOU?
DID TAY LIFT YOUR LEG, GRAB IT
UNDER THE KNEE?
>> FOR THE AMAZING RACE YOU
HAVE TO DO WEIRD POSES, SO...
>> ARE YOU A GOOD GO TO?
>> WHAT DID YOU THINKER, I'M A
DIRECTOR?
>> ARE YOU JEALOUS I'M IN THE
ENQUIRER?
>> TORY.
>> FOR SURE.
>>
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THE PRESIDENT'S DAUGHTER IS
SLAMMING AN ART EXHIBIT RIGHT
NOW AS SEXIST.
THIS IS THE ART EXHIBIT IN D.C.
IT INVITES PEOPLE TO THROW
CRUMBS AT A LOOKALIKE MODEL OF
IVANKA AND THEN VACUUMS THE
YUMS UP.
SHE WAS ASKED ON G.M.
A. HERE IS HER RESPONSE.
>> I THINK IT IS A VERY SEXIST
REPRESENTATION OF A WOMAN BUT
WHAT BOTHERED ME ABOUT THIS
IMAGE IS THAT THEY HIRED A 16-
YEAR-OLD GIRL TO STAND THERE
AND HAVE CRUMBS THROWN AT HER
FOR TWO HOURS A DAY FOR A
COUPLE OF MONTHS.
>> SO I HAVE A REAL PROBLEM
WITH THAT.
>> AND TORY, NOT ONLY ARE YOU
OUR LEGAL EAGLE BUT YOU'RE AN
ART HISTORY MAJOR.
SHOULD IVANKA HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH THIS?
>> NO.
I THINK SHE IS TAKING IT WRONG
AS THE VACUUM IS SEX EXIST.
THEY ARE NOT THROWING CRUMBS AT
HER OR THE LOOKALIKE.
THE WHOLE IDEA WHO IS THE
ARTIST IS IT IS MAKING FUN OF
US, THE VIEWERS WHO ARE
THROWING THE BREADCRUMBS SO SHE
HAS TO CLEAN UP THE MESS AND IT
SHOWS HOW MUCH WE ENJOY THE
MESS, AND TO WATCH IT BE
CLEANED UP.
HER CLEANING UP HER FATHER OR
THE ADMINISTRATION.
>> YES AND WE KEEP THROWING
STUFF AT HER TO SEE WHAT SHE
WILL CLEAN UP.
IT IS A VERY BIG
INTERPRETATION.
I THINK SHE USED TOO MUCH OF A
LITERAL INTERPRETATION.
IT IS PROF VACATION.
>> BUT SOME PEOPLE WITH ART,
YOU HAVE EVERY RIGHT TO THE
INTERPRETATION.
YOU HAD A DIFFERENT
>> YES.
I'M SURPRISED BY YOUR REACTION
IN THIS ME TOO MOVE: THIS IS
KIND OF SEXIST.
I DON'T THINK A WOMAN WITH A
VACUUM IS IN ANY WAY
ENLIGHTENING.
I GET THE ART FORM BUT I DON'T
THINK IT IS COOL.
>> WHAT ARE WORDS YOU THINK OF?
>> '60s.
ANTIQUE QUITED.
>> EXACTLY.
>> SO THAT IS THE POINT.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SEE HER AS
THIS ROLE MODEL, 1950s "LEAVE
IT TO BEAVER" ON THE OUTSIDE,
BUT ON THE INSIDE SHE IS
CLEANING UP EVERY BODY'S MESS
AND THERE IS THAT "LEAVE IT TO
BEAVER."
>> BUT BECAUSE IT IS TRUMP,
THEY INTERPRET IT AS ART BUT IF
IT WAS THE OBAMAS IT WOULDN'T
BE INTERPRETED THAT WAY.
>> IF IT WAS MICHELLE OR
SOMETHING I DON'T THINK THEY
WOULD HAVE BEEN ANGRY BUT
HOPEFULLY INTERPRETED IT AS AN
ART PIECE.
>> WE INTERPRET IT DIFFERENT.
>> WE HAVE SAD NEWS TO SHARE.
ACTOR ALBERT FINNEY PASSED AWAY
AT 82.
HE RECEIVED FIVE OSCAR
NOMINATIONS FOR HIS ROLES IN
TOM JONES, MURDER ON THE ORIENT
EXPRESS AND ERIN BROCKOVICH AND
HE WAS IN ANNIE.
I LOVED HIM IN BIG FISH.
HIS FAMILY SAID HE PASSED AWAY
PEACEFULLY AFTER A SHORT
ILLNESS WITH THOSE CLOSEST TO
HIM BAY HIS SIDE.
WE'RE ALSO REMEMBERING FRANK
ROBINSON, HE WAS THE FIRST
AFRICAN-AMERICAN MANAGER IN
MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL.
HE PASSED AWAY.
HE WON MVP IN BOTH LEAGUES.
>> I ALWAYS LOOK AT YOU,
BECAUSE YOU FOCUS ON THEIR
LEGACY.
>> WE NOT THAT IS WAITING FOR
ALL OF US.
THE ONLY THING WE CAN CONTROL
IS WHAT WE'RE DOING RIGHT NOW.
HOW YOU HANDLE TODAY.
YOU LOOK AT THE LIVES THAT
FRANK ROBINSON HAD AND, I MEAN,
WHAT ELSE DO YOU WANT?
BUT PASS AWAY AT HOME WITH YOUR
GRANDKIDS AROUND THE BED.
THAT IS COOL.
THAT IS THE GOAL.
IT IS NOT COOL WHEN YOU'RE 20
AND YOU'RE OUT AT THE NIGHTCLUB
AND SOMETHING HAPPENS.
WHEN YOU ARE AT HOME AND GET TO
DIE WITH THE PEOPLE WHO LOVE
YOU, I'M ALL FOR THAT.
>> AMEN.
>> WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>> THIS FEBRUARY, "DAILY BLAST
LIVE" AND SANDALS RESORTS WANT
YOU TO FALL IN LOVE ALL OVER
AGAIN.
WE'RE GIVING AWAY A TRIP FOR
YOU AND YOUR SPECIAL SOMEONE TO
ONE OF SANDALS LUXURY INCLUDED
VACATION HOT SPOTS.
JUST WATCH DBL FOR THE WORD OF
THE DAY AND GO TO "DAILY BLAST
LIVE.COM"/SANDALS TO ENTER.
THE MORE WORDS, THE MORE
CHANCES TO WIN.
THE WINNER WILL BE ANNOUNCED
LIVE ON DBL FEBRUARY 27th.
HOW COULD YOU NOT LOVE THAT?
>>> "BEST FIENDS."
COLLECT JO JO AND TONS OF OTHER
CUTE CHARACTERS.
SOLVE THOUSANDS OF FUN PUZZLES
KS DOWNLOAD "BEST FIENDS" TODAY
FOR FREE.
BEST FRIENDS WITHOUT THE "R."
"BEST FIENDS."
>>> SNACKING HAS NEVER BEEN
THIS EXCITING.
TO GET YOUR OWN FREE SAMPLER
BOX GO TO GRAZE.COM AND ENTER
EAT 56 AND
>>> WELCOME BACK TO DBL.
THEY ARE CRACKING DOWN OF THE
POSTING AND SHARES CHECKPOINTS
>>> THEY SENT A CEASE AND
DESIST LETTER TO GOOGLE TO STOP
SHARING THIS.
THE DEPARTMENT SAYS POSTING THE
LOCATIONS OF DWI CHECKPOINTS IS
LIKELY GROUNDS FOR ENGAGING IN
CRIMINAL CONDUCT BECAUSE IT
COULD BE USED TO AID IMPAIRED
AND INTOXICATED DRIVERS AND
BYPASSING CHECKPOINTS AND
ENCOURAGES THAT DRIVING.
>>> CHASTITY FROM FACEBOOK SAYS
THE APP DOESN'T NECESSARILY
SHOW COLLECT POINTS.
IT IS ALLOWS PEOPLE TO TIP-OFF
OTHER DRIVERS WHERE THE POLICE
ARE LOCATED.
THEY ARE MAKING IT SOUND LIKE
THEY ARE EXPOSING CHECKPOINTS.
IT TRULY HELPS ME SLOW DOWN
WHEN I'M DRIVING.
>> LOOK AT YOU WITH THE
CONSPIRACY THEORY.
THAT SOUNDS RIGHT FOR DUIs ARE
A BIG SOURCE OF REVENUE FOR
POLICE AN WELL AS SPEEDING
TICKETS.
WHEN THEY SAY A COP IS 100 FEET
AHEAD, THEY DON'T LIKE THAT.
>> YOU WANT TO GO HIGHER WITH
YOUR VOICE?
>> I WAS HURT.
>>
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> SHOCKED.
>> I AM SO SORRY.
KAREN SAID IT HAS TO DO WITH
THE GOTCHA MENTALITY OF THE
COPS.
>> SOMETHING VERY INTERESTING
FOR ME IS YOU AREN'T ALLOWED TO
STOP A CAR UNLESS YOU HAVE
PROBABLE CAUSE BECAUSE YOU HAVE
RIGHTS TO PRIVACY WHICH I'M BIG
ON.
SO IF YOU HAVE A D.U.I.
CHECKPOINT WHERE THEY CHECK
EVERY CAR, THEY HAVE TO
ANNOUNCE IT SO EVERY STATE YOU
HAVE TO HEAR FROM THE POLICE IF
YOU HAVE A SCANNER.
ALL THEY ARE DOING IS PUTTING
IT IN THERE.
I WANT MY PRIVACY KEPT CLEAN.
>> BUT WHAT ABOUT IF YOUR
PRIVACY IS INFRINGING ON THE
SAFETY OF MY LOVED ONES?
I HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THAT.
WHEN IT COMES TO DRINKING AND
DRIVING I HAVE ZERO TOLERANCE
AND FOR DECADES WE HAVE HAD
THESE CHECKPOINTS AND THEY HAVE
LEGITIMATELY TAKEN PEOPLE OFF
THE ROAD THAT COULD HAVE KILLED
ONE OF MY LOVED ONES, SO I
AGREE.
I DON'T THINK WA ZE SHOULD BE A
RED FLAG WHERE THE CHECKPOINTS
ARE.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH THEY
ARE LOOKING OUT FOR OUR SAFETY.
I THINK IT IS A MINI PLAY.
>> BUT THE END RESULT IS TAKING
THEM OFF THE ROAD.
>> IF YOU'RE DRIVING DRUNK,
YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
UBERS ARE $5.
>> BUT SOME PEOPLE LIVE
PAYCHECK TO PAYCHECK.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DRINKING FOR
THEN.
>> JUST TAKE AN UBER.
>>> COMING UP, WE HAVE THE MUST
HAVE GIFTS THAT WILL WOW YOUR
SWEETHEART THIS V DAY.
NEXT WE'RE CHATTING WITH THE
STARS OF THE LATEST PROJECT.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK WITH
THAT.
>>> HI.
I'M MATT McCOY.
FOR PEOPLE AS EXPERIENCED AS
YOU AND ME, CAREFUL DRIVING
COMES NATURALLY.
ALL THAT EXPERIENCE SHOULD BE
WORTH SOMETHING AND IT IS.
WITH THE AARP AUTO INSURANCE
PROGRAM FROM THE HARTFORD.
SWITCHING SAVED ME HUNDREDS.
FOUR OF FIVE MEMBERS 50 AND
OVER WHO SWITCHED FROM
COMPANIES LIKE ALLSTATE, STATE
FARM AND GEICO, GOT A LOWER
RATE WITH THE HARTFORD.
>> I GOT BETTER POLICY AND
COVERAGE AND A BETTER RATE AS
WELL.
>> DRIVERS 50 AND OVER LIKE TO
SAVE MONEY, BUT IT IS GREAT
WHEN IT COMES WITH COVERAGE AND
BENEFITS DESIGNED FOR US.
THAT IS REAL VALUE.
CALL FOR YOUR FREE QUOTE.
NOT AN AARP MEMBER, THE
HARTFORD HELPS YOU JOIN IN
MINUTES.
THEY RESPECT THE CUSTOMERS
ENOUGH TO DO THE RIGHT THING,
LIKE WITH NEW KARRIE  KNEW CAR
SPACE REPLACEMENT.
THEY WILL PAY THE FULL COST.
SOMETIMES LIFE HAPPENS AND WHEN
IT DOES, IT IS IMPORTANT TO
KNOW THE BUSINESS YOU'RE DOING
BUSINESS WITH HAS YOUR BACK.
THEY HAVE MY BACK.
>> THEY OFFER LIFETIME RENEW
BUILT.
THAT IS THE HARTFORD'S PROMISE
NOT TO DROP YOU EVEN IF YOU
HAVE HAD AN ACCIDENT.
>> IT IS A GREAT FEELING AND
COMFORTABLE FEELING TO KNOW I'M
NOT GOING TO GET DROPPED FOR
THAT REASON.
>> I FEEL LIKE I HAVE A PARTNER
IN THE HARTFORD AND I CAN TRUST
THEM WHEN AND IF I NEED THEM.
>> YOU CAN SAVE HUNDREDS OF
DOLLARS IF YOU SWITCH AND GET
NEW KARRIE PLACEMENT AND
LIFETIME RENEW BUILT.
>> I WOULD RECOMMEND THE
HARTFORD TO FRIENDS, RELATIVES,
ANYBODY.
>> CERTAINLY WHEN WE NEEDED
THEM, THEY WERE THERE FOR US.
ITS IMPRESSIVE.
>> CALL 1(800)683-7118 TO
REQUEST YOUR FREE QUOTE.
THAT IS 1(800)683-7118 OR GO TO
GO HARTFORD AUTO.COM.
>> THE WATCH AND WIN WORD IS
INCLUSIVE.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO DBL.
CRITICS ARE CALLING JAMES
CAMERON'S NEWEST MOVIE
MESMERIZING AND ASTONISHING.
IT IS THE LATEST ATTEMPT AT
PUSHING HIGH-TECH BOUNDARIES
AFTER HIS 2009 SHOW AVATAR.
>>> THIS BODY, I FEEL A
CONNECTION TO IT.
I CAN'T EXPLAIN.
>> HELLO, EVERYONE.
>> HELLO.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> I SAW YOU IN ACTION AND I
CAN ONLY IMAGINE HOW HARD IT
MUST HAVE BEEN TO KISS SOMEONE
THROUGH A KIND OF MOTION SUIT.
HOW IS THAT?
>> SEXY.
>> WAS THERE ANY TONGUE ACTION
OR LIKE A CLAW IN A MASK?
>> NO, NO.
MY FACE IS RIGHT THERE.
FOR BETTER OR WORSE, THAT IS ME
UP THERE.
>> WHAT IS IT LIKE DIRECTING
SOMEONE WHO IS THERE THAT YOU
CAN'T SEE THE FINAL THING IN
THAT MOMENT?
>> TOUCH HIM AGAIN AND I WILL
KILL YOU.
>> IT WAS KIND OF DAUNTING.
I WAS WONDERING WHAT IS MY
ACTRESS GOING TO EVEN LOOK LIKE
BECAUSE I'M SO USED TO ROSA
BEING THERE.
IT WAS LIKE WHAT IF I DON'T
LIKE HER AS MUCH AND WHEN IT
WAS DONE, IT WAS LIKE OH IT IS
ROSA.
IT IS STILL ROSA EVEN THOUGH
THE PROPORTIONS ARE DIFFERENT,
IT IS A DIFFERENT FACE.
>> LAST NIGHT I SAW YOU KISS
SOMEONE THAT WASN'T ACTUALLY
THERE.
>> THAT IS LIKE THE ULTIMATE
CATFISH.
>> HELLO FELLOW LONDONER.
>> HELLO DARLING.
>> WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE TO DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT MAYBE WHEN
TECHNOLOGY GETS THAT FAR I'LL
BE LIKE ACTUALLY I WANT MY
WHOLE BLOOMING BODY.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
CHATTING.
>> WHAT WAS IT'S LIKE PLAYING
SUCH A DIFFERENT CHARACTER AND
WHAT DO YOU PREFER THE MEAN GUY
OR THE LOVING FATHER FIGURE?
>> WHY WOULD THAT BE A
CONTRADICTION?
MEAN GUYS CAN BE LOVING FATHERS
AND LOVING FATHERS CAN BE MEAN.
EVERYBODY HAS EVERYTHING.
IT IS JUST THE PROPORTION THAT
TO WHICH IT IS DISTRIBUTED IN
1%NAL TY IS WHAT I'M CALLED
UPON TO DISCOVER AS AN ACTOR.
>> CAN I ASK YOU A BOUGHT BEING
A DOCTOR IN THE NAVY?
WHAT SIDE WOULD YOU WANT TO
BETTER YOURSELF?
>> THAT WOULD DEPEND WHAT I
NEED.
I'M WELL SERVED WITH WHAT I
HAVE GOT.
I LIKE BEING A HUMAN TRYING TO
MAKE WHAT I HAVE WORK PROPERLY.
>> BUT THIS TIME YOU'RE SO
LOVING AND SO SWEET AND  --
THAT IS WHO I REALLY AM.
>> ARE YOU TELLING ME THE
TRUTH?
>> NO.
>> WHAT YOU THINK YOU KNOW
ABOUT ME FROM WATCHING OTHER
MOVIES, COME ON.
REALLY?
>>
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> GREAT INTERVIEW.
OUR DIGITAL TEAM POSTED A
REVIEW OF THE MOVIE.
CHECK IT OUT ON OUR YouTUBE
PAGE.
COMING UP, SHE DROPS IT IN THE
BIG BROTHER HOUSE.
FIND OUT HOW SHE IS HELPING
OTHERS DROP THE POUNDS AND KEEP
THEM OFF.
NEXT IN OUR DBL HEALTH BLAST.
>>> PROMOTIONAL CONSIDERATION
IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY...
WOULDN'T YOU LIKE TO WAKE UP
EVERY MORNING WITH HAIR THAT
LOOKS HEALTHY, FULL AND
BEAUTIFUL?
WELL NOW, YOU CAN WITH
CLINICALLY PROVEN VIVISCAL, THE
NUMBER ONE DRUG FEEL SUPPLEMENT
MADE FOR EVERY WOMAN OF EVERY
HAIR TYPE.
IN AS LITTLE AS THREE MONTHS IT
CAN INCREASE VOLUME BY 30% AND
SHEDDING BY 40% GUARANTEED.
RIGHT NOW A THREE MONTH SUPPLY
OF THE VIVISCAL ADVANCED HAIR
HEALTH SUPPLEMENTS CAN BE YOURS
FOR THE LOW PRICE OF ONLY
$39.99 FOR THE FIRST MONTH'S
SUPPLY AND FOR THE FIRST TIME
EVER WE'LL INCLUDE A FREE
VIVISCAL GORGEOUS EL KICK XOR.
GET ALL THESE GIFTS VALUED AT
OVER $100 FREE.
AND SHIPPING IS FREE.
CALL 1(800)950-3117 OR GO
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
%
>>> WELCOME BACK TO DBL.
TEN YEARS AGO ROBIN NICHOLS
MADE SIMPLE CHANGES TO HER LIFE
THAT LED TO AN INCREDIBLE
TRANSFORMATION.
SHE LOST MORE THAN 100 POUNDS
AND KEPT IT OFF.
BRANDON LONDON CAUGHT UP WITH
HER.
>>> HI ROBIN.
I'M BRANDON LONDON.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> THANK YOU FOR SHARING YOUR
STORY WITH DBL NATION.
YOU LOST 100 POUNDS TEN YEARS
AGO.
WHAT ARE SOME OF THE THINGS
THAT CAUSED YOU TO BECOME OVER
WEIGHT?
>> FROM AS EARLY AS I CAN
REMEMBER LOOKING AT PICTURES OF
MYSELF AS A BABY, I'M
OVERWEIGHT AND THERE IS FOOD IN
MY MOUTH AND THERE IS CHOCOLATE
OR ICE-CREAM AND I'M ASLEEP AND
COVERED IN STUFF.
>> WHEN DID YOU HIT ROCK
BUTTON?
>> AFTER THE BIRTH OF OUR
SECOND CHILD I WENT SHOPPING
AND I COULDN'T FIT IN THE
LARGER SIZE AND I REMEMBER
BEING LIKE OH, MY GOD.
I REMEMBER FORCING MYSELF TO
TAKE OFF ALL MY CLOTHES AND
LOOK AT MYSELF IN THE MIRROR
AND GRAB AT MYSELF AND BE LIKE
WHAT HAS BECOME OF YOU?
>> WHO ARE SOME OF THE PEOPLE
THAT HELPED YOU OUT AND
MOTIVATED YOU ALONG THE WAY?
>> MY DAD.
MY DAD WAS DEFINITELY HUGE.
MY SISTERS AND MY FAMILY HAVE
ALWAYS BEEN AMAZING.
I STARTED ROBIN'S NEST AS MUCH
TO KEEP MYSELF HEALTHY AND TO
HELP OTHERS SO I OFFER RETREATS
FOR PEOPLE WHO WILL COME STAY
WITH ME AND FOR 72 HOURS I COOK
FOR THEM AND DON'T ALLOW THEM
TO CHEAT AND GET THEM THROUGH
THE DETOX PROCESS.
>> HOW WERE YOU SO CONSISTENT
WHEN IT CAME TO THE 12-STEP
PROGRAM AND IT WASN'T A START
AND STOP THING?
>> I HIT ROCK BOTTOM.
MY DAD WAS DYING.
I HAD TO WATCH HIM DIE.
I WOULD ALWAYS USE FOOD TO
MITIGATE LIFE AND THERE IS
NOTHING ON EARTH THAT COULD
HAVE BEEN HARDER AND THAT IS
WHEN I WALKED INTO THE DOORS OF
THE 12 STEP PROGRAM AND WAS
LIKE PLEASE HELP ME.
>> HOW HAS YOUR LIFE CHANGED
OVER THE LAST TEN YEARS?
IN EVERY WAY.
I'M SKIING, TRYING THINGS I
NEVER WOULD HAVE.
I HAVE SO MUCH GRATITUDE TOR
LIFE.
>> YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO SHOW
US TODAY.
>> I DO.
I DO.
HERE IT IS.
YOU WANT ME TO PUT IT ON?
>> JUST PUT IT OUT REAL QUICK.
I WANT TO SEE THE
TRANSFORMATION FOR SURE.
WOW!
>> IT IS A PRETTY COLOR.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WOW!
WHAT CURRENT ROBIN RIGHT NOW
SAY TO THE ROBIN WHO WAS
WEARING THIS SWEATER?
>> IT REPRESENTS SO MUCH MORE
THAN JUST WEIGHT.
HIDING FROM LIFE AND IT IS
AMAZING TO TAKE IT OFF.
>> WELL, GO AHEAD AND TAKE OFF
THAT CHAIN.
HERE IS THE REBIRTH AND HERE
YOU ARE NOW.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
I'M THANKFUL FOR HEARING YOUR
STORY.
>> TO LIVE YOUR LIFE TO THE
FULLEST CALL 1(800)393-6540.
>> WHAT AN INCREDIBLE STORY.
I THINK THAT WILL INSPIRE A LOT
OF PEOPLE AND SEEING EVERYTHING
THAT SHE HAS OVERCOME IN THE
PAST ESPECIALLY WITH HER FATHER
AND IT IS NICE TO SEE SHE IS
TAKING AHOLD OF HER LIFE AND
ENDING UP ON TON.
>> GOOD FOR HER.
>> AND BRANDON LONDON WORKS SO
HARD FOR US AND HE IS GETTING
GREAT AT THESE PIECES.
>> SHE WAS SO COMFORTABLE
TALKING ABOUT THAT.
THE PASSING OF HER FATHER.
YOU SEE THAT WEIGHT.
WHEN PEOPLE SEE PEOPLE OVER
WEIGHT, THEY SAY SHE IS LAZY,
HE IS LAZY.
THERE IS SO MUCH PAIN UNDER
THAT WEIGHT AND GOOD ON HER AND
GREAT JOB BRANDON LONDON.
>> THAT WAS REALLY NICE.
>> WE NEED TO CONTINUE THAT
CONVERSATION IN THE BREAK.
IF YOU'RE LEAVING US RIGHT NOW,
YOU CAN STILL WATCH US LIVE ON
FACEBOOK AND YouTUBE.
HERE IS WHAT IS COMING UP NEXT.
>>> DINA LOEWENS MYSTERY MAN
>>> THE CELEBRITY BIG BROTHER
HOUSE GUEST SAYS SHE HAS BEEN
DATING HIM FOR FIVE YEARS, BUT
YOU WON'T BELIEVE THE ONE THING
THEY HAVE NEVER DONE.
THEN REALITY TV STAR AND
WEDDING PLANNER DAVID TUTERA.
THE CELEBRITY BRIDES TO BE.
HE IS DYING TO HELP.
VALENTINE'S DAY GIFTS THAT WILL
MELT YOUR HONEY'S HEART.
DON'T MISS
THIS PRESIDENTS DAY,
HAVERTYS IS HONORING
PRESIDENT MOM.
SHE MADE THE EXECUTIVE DECISION
TO BUY STORE BOUGHT COOKIES
FOR THE BAKE SALE.
SHE PARDONED EMMA FOR...
BEING EMMA.
AND THEN THERE WAS THE WHOLE
CONE CRISIS THING.
PRESIDENT MOM, THIS PRESIDENTS
DAY SALE IS FOR YOU!
FOR THE NEXT FOUR DAYS, GET
FREE FINANCING FOR FIVE YEARS.
GET BIG SAVINGS ON SOFAS, BEDS,
DINING SETS AND MORE.
NOW THAT'S FISCALLY RESPONSIBLE
LEADERSHIP.
HAVERTYS.
Life Looks Good.
na
wanna miss
tonight's twisted elimination,
especially if you're a fan
of revenge.
'Bout damn time!
(thunder rumbling)
♪ We represent
our hood tonight ♪
♪ Come on, we represent
our hood for life... ♪♪
(announcer)
Welcome back.
Let's get you caught up.
Morgan and Jay have worked
through their issues,
and are on the up and up.
What's my favorite
color today?
Pink.
Yup.
(announcer)
But Corey seems to be the pain
in their ass that won't go away.
Chad and Nicole's relationship
is moving to the next level,
taking each other's
measurements.
Wow, you (bleep) it up.
I had it.
No, here.
I got it.
I'm gonna measure it for you,
you (bleep) ding-a-ling.
(announcer)
Janelle's still running hot
after attacking Diandra
for kissing her ex Darian.
And Farrah's discovering her
ripped-up posters,
which was payback by Nurys
for being kicked in the cooter.
Oh, my God.
Someone came up here
and (bleep) up my signs.
All right, so that's
the (bleep) you started!
Did she (bleep) do this?
She might have
did it, Farrah.
Okay.
Well, this is the best one.
Did someone
(bleep) up my-- okay.
All right.
Don't attack all of my amazing,
amazing signs...
that my housemates spent
their time on making for me.
Did someone have an idea
to (bleep) bend all my signs?
■    I (bleep) did! I did!
I happily (bleep) did!
I did, I did, I did, I did!
Nurys did!
She kicked me.
She decided to put
her hands on me,
so I grabbed her
"free Farrah" posters
and I ripped them in half.
Stop! No!
You think I give a (bleep)?
No, no, no, no!
Nurys, no!
Diandra, Diandra!
I know!
If you wanna touch my stuff,
your (bleep) gets
a big "(bleep) you"
down the toilet.
Okay, touch my (bleep), bitch.
Touch it, I dare you.
somebody else's
(bleep).
(Nurys)
I did.
You ugly-ass bitch!
Oh, I'm ugly, bitch?
How much plastic surgery
have you had to fix your face
and your body?
I haven't done not one thing
to my body or my face
and I'm (bleep) gorgeous,
so (bleep) my (bleep), bitch.
(Farrah)
You (bleep)
disgusting bitch.
Sure, sure,
I'll take your (bleep).
I'll take your (bleep)
and put it in the toilet.
If she touches my (bleep),
I'm letting you guys know,
I'ma beat this bitch's ass.
Go ahead, Farrah.
Put that (bleep)
in the toilet.
o
Here it goes.
Here it (bleep) goes.
Come on, sis.
Here it goes.
Put that (bleep)
in the toilet.
She (bleep) bent every one.
She (bleep) your ex, sis!
(laughter)
She bent! She bent!
Disrespect me,
disrespect my stuff,
you will not be respected.
And, um, karma's a bitch.
Oh, (bleep)!
She ripped her (bleep).
Here we go. Here it goes.
Here you go.
Farrah's said
she ripped it all up.
If you argue with Farrah,
she will kick you in the vagina
and put your shoes in the toilet
and flush.
That's some pussy-ass (bleep).
I've never done something
so crazy like that.
It's bad enough that Farrah
already kicked me in the vagina.
Now she's grabbing my sneakers
and she flushes them
down the toilet.
I could've touched her makeup
that was there,
or any of her personal
belongings, and I didn't,
because I have some type
of class.
Don't threaten me!
Don't trip me!
Don't (bleep) attack me!
(announcer)
Since fighting is
a big fat no-no,
Janelle, Nurys, and Farrah are
sent to hotels for the night
with a warning.
Talk (bleep),
get hit, bitch.
0 4@@
I'll see you tomorrow
'cause we always
keepin' positive things.
I love you. Mwah!
Love you too.
♪♪
You guys think the, like,
Farrah-Nurys situation
is gonna continue today or--
Oh, yeah, 100%.
She's in a very precarious legal
situation right now.
Don't be coming around
kicking anyone.
But, like, I just got--
like, this is childish.
Okay, but if you got
kicked in the cooter,
what would you (bleep) do?
I'ma kick you back
in the cooter.
Farrah went back,
and then the security
guard was there.
She tripped over his feet
and Farrah fell on her ass.
Well, good thing she's got
those airbags back there.
No, she-- yeah.
Did she bounce?
(laughter)
♪♪
My ex is definitely
coming before yours.
One of 'em.
One of 'em is coming
and it's gonna
(bleep) up everything.
I don't want Chad's ex
coming into this house.
I will literally ruin
this girl's life
if she thinks for one second
that she has
any upper hand on me
when it comes to Chad.
I will rip her to shreds.
We still gotta have--
we're still going
to the sauna.
I know.
That's still a date.
Exes coming in.
■es, exes.
At the end of the day,
we're just these, like, what?
Skin blobs floating around
on this planet
that's going through space
through a round of ball of fire?
Like, and that's life,
and then you die.
You know, eventually.
(announcer)
Thanks for the deep thoughts,
Einstein.
We to that point yet?
Yeah.
We can have sex
really close to people?
We are?
Okay.
Come here, Corey.
We're gonna have sex
on top of you.
You're our first victim.
(Corey)
Those guys are so cute together.
I'm peanut butter and jealous
of their relationship.
I really don't have feelings
for Sh
And Morgan, she's kinda
boo'd up with Jay.
I'm peanut butter and jealous
of their relationship.
You know, hopefully I can findn
and be a cute couple.
(siren wailing)
(woman)
Oh, my God!
What relationships
are gonna get
messed up today?
Ahh!
Please not me.
I'ma say Morgan.
I'm feeling it.
Don't wield that (bleep).
Chad has not been
to the beach yet.
(Morgan)
It has to be Chad.
♪♪
(Nicole)
(bleep)!
(cheering)
Oh, my tits look so good!
(bleep)!
(bleep).
So who's the last person?
Please not me.
Please.
(bleep)!
(cheering)
(overlapping chatter)
Why?
Aw, damn it.
Oh, my God.
Just give me a little bit
of time before
another one comes.
Can I just enjoy my peace?
Bring up some men.
Bye, girls.
Bye.
Bye, Morgan.
■÷
Be good.
Good luck.
♪♪
(Morgan)I have so ms
in this house.
Like, Corey needs to go home.
So I am worried.
I feel like I have finally
gotten to a good place with Jay,
and I just-- I don't want an ex
to come and screw that up.
Best-case scenario is that
it's somebody else's ex,
not mine,
and I can just go back
in the house and have fun
with Chad,
and not have anybody try
interrupting my little
honeymoon.
How y'all feeling?
Terrible.
I'm clueless.
(Romeo)
You're clueless?
For sure.
I don't need
a third, Romeo.
I think me and Jay are
on good terms finally.
So Corey's not
confusing things for you?
Um, I just don't think
it's gonna work between
me and him.
Nicole, how are things
with you and Chad?
We're good.
I feel like you're gonna
(bleep) it up though,
so bring on the exes.
(Romeo)
By the end of this
whole experience,
some of you may find new love,
rekindle with an old love,
or just say (bleep) love.
But the real question:
Are you completely over your ex?
It's time.
No.
Let's bring 'em out.
(bleep).
My ex coming in?
Like, he doesn't need
to be here.
Just throw him back
in the water.
It's like, how much more
can I take?
I haven't cracked yet,
but I feel like if an ex
comes out of the water,
I might reach my cracking point.
♪♪
♪ Fun, everybody love a bomber,
balls are great... ♪
Oh, that's not my ex!
Yeah, that's not mine either.
♪ Go ahead,
treat yourself... ♪♪
My name is Monte,
from Memphis, Tennessee,
and you may know me from
"Big Brother: Over the Top."
Being a southern gentleman is
about treating a girl right.
Opening the door for her,
not cussing, acting a fool
in front of her,
but also smacking her ass
as she walks through the door.
Me and Morgan met
in the Big Brother house.
We dated for six months
and then she decided
she wants to move to L.A.,
so that kind of put a,
you know, rut in the groove.
I'm here to not only
rekindle me and Morgan,
but I know for a fact
that Morgan is the one
I wanna settle down with.
And I'm at that point in my life
where I'm ready.
What's up, man?
Doing good.
What's going on, Monte?
How do you like
seeing Morgan over there?
She looks pretty good, man.
Stop.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Why you here?
Gotta get her back, man.
Get her back?
Yeah.
He's trying to get you back!
Great opportunity
to take her back.
■/
It is, man.
Once in a lifetime.
Ugh!
What happened between
y'all two?
I ended up moving
to Los Angeles.
It was too much
of long distance
got in the way and--
So you left him hanging?
It was too hard being
so far apart.
Seeing Monte brings back
a lot of good memories.
We don't really have
any fights.
You real flustered
right now, like--
Yeah, G  because I'm alreG
with two exes,
You real flusand now you'reGg i.
right now, like--
But this connection
seem genuine right here.
Even from the other ones,
I'm feeling something.
I think there is
a genuine connection,
but it's difficult
because I got some issues
back at the house.
Don't play with Jay's feelings.
I think that this is something
between Jay and Morgan
that can potentially ruin them.
We got some things
to figure out.
I'm done.
(bleep), (bleep)!
No, Morgan!
(bleep)!
(sobbing)
Uh-oh!
Guess what day it is?
Guess what day it is!
Huh...anybody?
Julie!
Ah come on, I know
you can hear me.
Mike Mike Mike
Mike Mike...
what day is it Mike?
Ha ha ha ha!
Leslie, guess
what today is?
It's Hump Day.
Whoot Whoot!
Ronny, how happy are folks
who save hundred of dollars
switching to GEICO?
I'd say happier than
a camel on Wednesday.
HUMP DAY!!!
Get happy. Get GEICO.
Fifteen minutes could save
you fifteen percent or more.
Hy-a-luronic Acid
Hyaluronic acid.
It's the skincare ingredient
that everyone is searching for!
And It's in here.
New from Revitalift:
Derm Intensives Hyaluronic
Acid Serum
With our highest concentration
of Hyaluronic Acid in a serum
Visibly plumps skin in
just one week
bounce back!
And reduces wrinkles for
younger-looking skin.
Powerful results
Validated by a panel
of dermatologists
New Revitalift Derm Intensives
Hyaluronic Acid Serum
From L'Oreal Paris
[SFX]■■■■■WW■W■■é■
We're worth it.
[SFX]
♪
Introducing new
Hershey's Milk Chocolate
e's Pieces
Now in one bar
u's Pieces
♪♪
So how you been?
I've been good.
It's been an experience,
to say the least.
Um, I'll go ahead
and fill you in since Romeo
told me I need to be honest.
Yeah, shoot me straight.
Don't lie to me.
I feel like I'm
an emotional wreck at all times
in this house.
It's like I'm the only person
with three exes.
Some people don't even have one
ex and I'm dealing with three.
Like, I need to get Corey out
of this house, and he's honestly
pretty boring.
Jay came in the house.
I kind of rekindled things
with him.
Then Corey came in,
so it was kind of like...
Double whammy.
...a weird messy
love triangle.
But I thought I had it
figured out till you
walked up on the beach.
Me and Monte had a great
relationship before this.
It didn't end badly.
My family loves him.
He's unfortunately the exact
kind of guy that my dad
would want me to marry,
which is terrifying.
You're my girl.
Everything happens
for a reason.
So I really think,
you know,
Jay might be cool,
but, you know,
you gotta remember back
to what we had too.
We could rekindle that
even better.
I don't know who this
Jay guy is, but, uh,
he's gonna have to run
for his money, 'cause,
uh, Monte's coming.
Give me a fair shot.
That's all I ask.
Okay.
And I promise you,
you'll reconsider.
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ It♪ It's time to go, go,
go, go, whoa ♪
♪ Do you wanna,
do you wanna go? ♪♪
How you feeling though
this morning?
I'm cool.
Like, the only thing I was
actually, like, I was thinking
about, like, last night, was,
like, no one ever pulled her
to the side and was like,
"Yo, I understand you're upset,
but, like, how you're reacting,
like, that's not okay."
Depending on how Janelle
comes back from the hotel,
I'm hoping to see, uh,
a new-- a new person.
Uh, the girl that I
used to know.
Here we go.
Oh, (bleep)!
Oh, Nicole! Sha!
Chad, you're safe!
So Nicole is back now
and she doesn't have an ex,
and I'm just like,
"Thank God I don't have to deal
with that situation."
So how did the guy look?
Tell me.
Does he look cute
or whatever?
I'm kind of scared
for Jay.
(Janelle)
Why?
He said he's here
to get her back,
and he's here for no other
reason but to get her back.
(Chad)
Oh, (bleep).
Honestly, it should be called
"Morgan's Ex on the Beach."
Like, how many exes
do you have, girl?
Like, just stop.
(cheering)
(all exclaiming)
All right, pull the chair,
pull the chair, pull the chair.
Hold on.
Hey, Morgan.
Take a seat.
Let the man
do the talking.
Gah damn.
(laughter)
This Monte character?
(grunts) Damn!
Ugh!
Um, I will say this.
All the boys you
brought into the house
are fine as (bleep).
And-- yes.
So at least
I have good taste.
What are you here for?
What are your intentions?
What are my intentions?
Are you here to be with her?
■÷  Are ■;  to rekindle that fi?
Hell yeah, man.
I'm gonna rekindle the fire.
What are you talking about?
Okay, there we go.
"Oh, I'm gonna be just Mr. Tough
Guy here to steal your girl.
"I'ma flirt with her in front
of you and I'm gonna pretend
like I'm not.
Ha ha! I'm so cool!"
Clown.
If things don't work out
with Jay,
are we allowed to take him
into our relationship?
(laughter)
You're allowed to take him
right now if you want.
We can share.
(announcer)
Oh, God, it's so sweet
it's making me sick.
Let's see if everyone else
can be so levelheaded
as Janelle, Farrah, and Nurys
return from their stay
at the hotel.
Baby, baby, baby!
Hey!
ç■■7■7's Janelle.
Whoo!
What's up?
So I've had a night
to cool down, relax.
Going in the house, for me,
it is stressful
because I'm dealing
with the fact
that I really am, like,
heartbroken for real.
Diandra, can I talk to you?
Yes.
My main point
to pull Diandra aside
was to apologize to her
and let her know that, hey,
I know we've had our beefs
in the past.
Like, I know we personally
don't care for each other,
but the attack I made on her
was not personal at all.
So basically I just wanted
to genuinely apologize
for putting my hands on you.
Like, my issues are with him.
Like, I should conduct myself
better just as a human being.
You (bleep) kiss her?!
You're gonna kiss her?!
That is her ex.
Oh, (bleep).
Oh, you ain't tell me that.
(bleep) you laughing,
bitch?!
Janelle! Janelle! Janelle!
You (bleep)hole!
So I apologize.
I accept your apology.
Um, I wasn't
laughing at you.
Like, I'm sorry.
Like, when I get nervous,
I'm like...
(nervous chuckle)
But I literally--
all I said, I looked back,
like, this is crazy.
And thankful that you came
to apologize for putting
your hands on me.
No problem.
Like, I meant it, but I
shouldn't be hitting people.
I saw Janelle go up to Diandra,
apologize for the whole thing,
argument they had,
and just literally broke down.
And you know what?
It takes a grown person
to apologize and to admit that.
I accept your apology.
With me, if someone says sorry
and they genuinely mean it,
■     I will forgi
With me,Will I forget?ys sorry
and No. I'm not stupid. it,
I will definitely keep
my eyes up open,
but the minute you say sorry,
all right, clean slate.
I'ma do a handshake.
Okay.
We'll take it slow.
Yes.
Okay. Okay, thank you.
All right.
(announcer)
Now that Janelle and Diandra are
on the same page,
the house vibes seem to be
in a good place.
Maybe Farrah and Nurys
can squash their beef too?
Hello, house.
Hey, Farrah.
Hello.
There's another one.
So I'm back today
and I'm going in the house
and I'm just staying away
from literally everything,
everyone, and (bleep) them.
Aww.
Have a drink.
I'm back.
(screaming)
(laughter)
I'm extremely happy
that Nurys came back here.
She did nothing wrong,
but I understand as to why
she had to leave.
But I am genuinely upset
that Farrah is still here.
I'm gonna go ahead and leave it
in the fate of the Lord
and He will take care of that.
Karma's a bitch.
(indistinct chatter)
Good.
So if I started talking
to another girl,
she'd probably find out.
Hey, can we talk?
Hi, how are you?
Sure.
In private?
Okay.
I don't have
to (bleep) apologize
because I reacted like
a normal human being,
but better than a normal
human being,
'cause a normal human being
wouldn't have stopped
(bleep) hitting her.
(announcer)
Actually, a normal human being
probably wouldn't kick someone
in the vagina.
I guess I just wanted
to ask where your head
was at yesterday.
'Cause I'm confused
as to where all that
animosity came from.
All that, like--
Okay, so I'm
not confused.
I'm very aware about
what happened yesterday.
When I come in
to just hear what
my friend's ex-boyfriend
is saying,
all I'm hearing is insults,
um, from you about me,
acting like you know me.
I think--
That all was brought up
afterwards, so that's not
what we're talking about.
And continuation of that
and that was--
No, see, now you're
trying to play victim.
That's not what
we're gonna do.
So I'm not a victim.
So I know you
were just drinking.
I'm not drinking.
Okay. Okay.
I'm wide awake.
I have no patience for that.
I apologized for you
insulting me, you touching me.
No.
See, that's that--
no, no.
And I'm the bigger woman.
Okay. Ha, okay.
So I'm a real woman who knows
what really happened.
Okay, okay.
You're out of control.
Oh, my God.
She's literally
delusional.
So stop.
Get in control.
This bitch is delusional, yo.
Okay!
Farrah does not care abo anye
except for herself and s■■@@@@@.
■d■d■d■d■d■d■d■d■d■d■d■■d■■d■■d.
(Nurys)
Bitch, you're the trash.
You kicked me in the vagina
because I was having
a conversation
with someone.
Like, (bleep) psychotic.
Get ahold of yourself,
out-of-control groupie.
What's wrong?
No, she's still lying
and is a trash can.
I know I'm a bigger person.
She's a whore.
Do I need to apologize
to someone
who put that on themselves,
who caused that for themselves,
who (bleep) deserves worse
than what she got?
No.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Voluptuous Volume.
Intense Length.
Feathery-Soft Lashes.
This is what
paradise looks like.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Take your lashes to paradise.
Hello, there.
Do we go crunchy-cool
or golden Classic?
I know.
One for me and
one for you.
Now that's a sandwich!
Lay's.
Make Life Flavorful.
♪ Seed to the oat, to the O ♪
♪ To the honey in each bite ♪
♪ Healthy hearts make life
sweeter ♪
♪ So you can live it right ♪
♪ The good goes arouaround  andA
It's time for some
Straight Talk.
Hallelujah,
it's tax refund time.
So what are you going to do with
all that glorious extra money?
No, not that!
Here's a better plan.
Try Straight Talk Wireless and
get 25 gigs of high-speed data
for just $45 bucks a month.
That's right, all on America's
best 4G LTE networks.
Plus, save up to 200 dollars on
a Samsung Galaxy S9
with in-store activation.
Straight Talk Wireless.
Everything for less.
■■#    Your skin deserves bette.
Garnier Micellar Cleansing Water
with micelles that
work like a magnet.
It's a pure way to remove
stubborn makeup
without harsh rubbing.
Cleansing, reinvented.
Micellar Water.
By Garnier,
Naturally!
Every year,
Team Rubicon enlists the help
of veterans to provide relief
Every year,
to communities
affected by natural disasters.
Do it for those
who need■á■■
Mountain Dew
is proud
to support
the efforts
of
Team Rubicon.
Let's Do.
Juicy, sizzling steak.
Hand-tossed original dough.
Fresh cut onions,
crunchy green peppers,
a delicious
four cheese blend,
and our creamy Philly sauce.
All on the best
Philly Cheesesteak
you can get on a pizza.
Right now get
the new Philly
or any large specialty
Papa John's pizza
for just 12 bucks.
The iPhone XR is a marvel in
technology.
Yeah.
This edge to edge screen is
unbelievable.
Am I nuts or does everything
look better on an iPhone?
Both.
And with our Unlimited plan,
people can choose the best in
entertainment.
HBO, Cinemax, Showtime...
STARZ, VRV, Amazon Music, or
Pandora...
Now people can get what
they want.
Because everyone's different.
I feel like we shouldn't talk
for a couple of days.
AT&T has the only unlimited plan
that gives you your choice of
top-tier entertainment.
Get an iPhone XR on us when
you buy the latest iPhone.
MORE FOR YOUR THING. THAT'S OUR
THING.
I know it's hard Maddie.
But I promise,
it's gonna get better.
♪ ♪
(mom giggles)
This bitch
is delusional, yo.
It's (bleep) delusional.
Trash can!
Trash?
Have you seen the way
that you carry yourself?
Wow, like, what are you--
What the (bleep)?
Trash can outside
is a liar.
Now, you don't kick nobody in
the vagina, point blank, period.
Save vaginas!
(announcer)
ops to
for at
You know what would solve
all these problems?
A nice family dinner
just like mom used to make.
(overlapping chatter and toasts)
(cheering)
I think this is the last supper
before the storm.
(all)
Yes.
So, Jesus, take it away.
Jesus, stand up.
Take the wheel, Jesus!
♪♪
(overlapping shouting)
(alarm blaring)
(bleep)!
Oh, my God, here we go.
Chad, you gotta (bleep) read.
"Exes, you can't have dinner
without dessert."
I knew it!
Oh!
Some (bleep) about to pop off,
man, I can just smell it.
"Head down to the Shack
of Secrets to satisfy
your sweet tooth."
Exes?
All of us?
(Chad)
All the exes.
(overlapping chatter)
Welcome to hell!
♪♪
Whoo!
There can't be a bunch
of singles without
getting rid of some of us.
No, this is, like,
gonna be (bleep) up.
I can feel it.
Who got the best hearing?
You two.
Tell us.
Positive vibes.
Poibes.
"While you served the singles
dishes, they were busy
serving disses."
Oh...
"Press play to find out."
What's his name?
Nelson does not care
about Nurys.
He said that she was always
the side chick, the one that he
would just hit up to (bleep).
Ooh!
We play the video
and it's all of the OG singles
talking (bleep) about us exes.
Diandra, she's a smart one,
but that's not gonna save you
from all these cuts
you about to get, bitch.
She's a rude
(bleep) bitch.
We didn't order a (bleep)
hooker on demand.
Bitch!
Don't call me a hooker
when you're a porn star.
Can I combine
Jay's personality
with Corey's, like, looks?
Morgan, it's you saying Jay's
personality with Corey's looks,
you would combine it.
You're so (bleep).
(laughs)
No, I'm actually so (bleep).
And then I would literally have
my perfect man.
(bleep).
(Jay)
No!
You don't freaking say that!
If you"Why am I giving you
en y many chances?"'s like
Because you have treated me like
(bleep) on, like, every level.
And I'm just getting sick of it.
I like you.
So this is what
you wanted.
Like, what's--
how's that make you feel?
Confused.
I wish you would've
said that from the get-go.
No.
(Morgan grunting)
She told you she
didn't kiss anyone?
(grunts)
"Exes, can the singles have
their cake and eat it too?
Bring it to the table
and serve it up to find out."
Let's do it.
Whoo!
Hey, man.
No, it's all good.
No, no matter
what happens here,
I'm not gonna
bull(bleep) you
about that.
I'll tell straightforward.
I know that.
I feel really bad
for Jay right now.
'Cause I can imagine
being a man hearing that,
saying you're only half
of what I want.
If I,
and it's making me contemplate
what kind of person
Morgan i
I've only been here
for two hours and this place
is losing its mind.
I am already starting to see
it looks like a hornet's nest.
Whoo!
Dessert time, people!
So they bring up
this big pink cake,
and I'm like, "Thank you?"
We just heard a lot of people
like to have their cake...
And eat it too.
...and eat it too, people.
(bleep) that.
The exes already have a face on,
and y'all just came from
the Shack of Secrets
and y'all looking at us like
y'all just seen a dead ghost.
Downstairs we saw
every conversation
anybody ever talked (bleep)
about us.
Jay's face looks like
he just saw, like,
a million dead puppies.
I thing in his eyes
I've never seen before.
Farrah, you said that you didn't
know that they hired a hooker,
calling me a hooker.
Are you (bleep)--
I haven't said anything
different when I was
yelling yesterday.
No, honey,
I am not a hooker.
But you're a porn star!
How can you even have
your opinion?
I am not a hooker.
The next person
that calls me--
Do not call me a hooker,
because you do not know me...
(bleep)!
...because you were the one
masturbating on a video!
(bleep) you.
Okay?
That's all I can say
about that.
If a ex pop out,
I (bleep).
Wait, I think
thaI think it is.■■at's what
Ohh...
Pretty sure that's a bottle.
Girl, get--
get them hands dirty, honey.
Oh, (bleep), (bleep), (bleep).
(indistinct chatter)
(bleep).
Wow!
(all exclaiming)
So we got another message,
and I'm thinking like,
pssh, ain't nothing good
gonna come out of this.
We haven't had no good news yet
in that damn bottle, man.
"And now for the icing
on the cake.
"Because revenge
is a dish best served cold,
"it's time to flip the script.
Exes, you now have the power."
(cheers and applause)
That's some (bleep).
Nice!
We find out that the exes
going to get the power
to send one single home.
And I'm thinking...
oh, (bleep)!
Tables have turned, bitches,
and I'm here to come for each
and every one of you.
♪♪
■88■■■■■■■■?■qq■q■qq■■q■■■■■■■■2
Not much here,
except the usual.
Wh
things up a bit?
Alexa...
"Fire"
by The Ohio Players
♪Fire (uh) (uh)♪
What if we turn it up a notch?
♪Fire (It's all about) (Uh, uh)♪
What if we go off the map?
♪Fire (Woo, woo, woo)♪
♪Fire♪
The all-new RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
Hello, there.
Do we go crunchy-cool
or golden Classic?
I know.
One for me and
one for you.
Now that's a sandwich!
Lay's.
Make Life Flavorful.
You can't put a price on love.
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
Hy-a-luronic Acid
Hyaluronic acid.
It's the skincare ingredient
that everyone is searching for!
And It's in here.
New from Revitalift:
Derm Intensives Hyaluronic
Acid Serum
With our highest concentration
of Hyaluronic Acid in a serum
Visibly plumps skin in
just one week
bounce back!
And reduces wrinkles for
younger-looking skin.
Powerful results
Validated by a panel
of dermatologists
New Revitalift Derm Intensives
Hyaluronic Acid Serum
From L'Oreal Paris
We're worth it.
♪♪
(announcer)
Welcome back.
(cheers and ap)
■w■er)
Now that the exes have
the power,
one of you (bleep)-talking
singles is going home.
About time!
So I'm confused what the (bleep)
is happening here,
but you gotta let me knSpicy!
I mean, you just (bleep) up
my whole damn dinner.
(Morgan)
Jay? Jay?
(bleep) has hit the fan
and I've been trying
to make it work with Jay.
And I'm like, at this point,
I don't think I'm gonna be able
to dig myself out of this one.
(whispering in)
I'm done.
(bleep) (bleep) no.
No, no, no, Morgan.
No, I'm done.
Morgan!
(all exclaim)
Oh, (bleep)!
No, like, I'm done, no, like--
Morgan, Morgan.
I'm literally done.
No, I'm done.
I mean, Morgan, my girl,
I don't know what you've done
karma-wise, but God bless you.
■ ■     May the Force be
with you, dear.
(announcer)
In a living room far, far away,
the exes lean into the dark side
as they strategize
which single
they should get revenge on.
I know you're
gonna say Farrah,
but you gotta look at it
from this point of view.
Yeah, she causes
a lot of (bleep),
but y'all let her.
Like, y'all let-- listen.
Y'all let her words
actually eat up.
Y'all, y'all take,
like-- y'all act like
her words matter.
You only got here yesterday.
That's what I'm saying.
Mm-hmm.
You haven't seen
the whole thing about her.
She is nasty
as a human being.
Nasty.
I haven't really got an
opportunity to talk to Darian.
He was hanging around
Malcolm a lot,
and everyone knows that Malcolm
comes with Diandra and Nurys.
You're not making it easy for me
to forgive you,
because I'm continuously
watching you around people
that I don't like.
♪♪
(sobbing)
I just don't think it's fair!
Morgan, you are much stronger
than this, babe.
Come on!
Okay.
You know what?
I said this whole entire time
I was not gonna reach
my breaking point.
And congratulations,
"Ex on the Beach."
You officially broke me.
What else can I do
to screw up?
I feel like
I screw up everything!
No.
No, you don't.
Just let her cry.
She just needs to cry,
honestly.
Let it out.
I think right now Morgan
actually feels
genuinely sorry and bad.
She hurt Jay's feelings,
and I think Jay has every reason
to feel the way he does.
♪♪
■■■■■■■■■■  (bleep)!
(sustained bleep echoing)
Now, eyeliner goes NYC-proof.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil
from Maybelline New York.
Smudge resistant.
Sweat resistant.
Waterproof.
Up to 36-hour we
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil.
Only from Maybelline New York.
Every year,
Team Rubicon enlists the help
eterans to provide relief
to communities
affenatural disasters.
Do it for those
who need your help.
Mountain Dew
is proud
to support
the efforts
of
Team Rubicon.
Let's Do.
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
Hello, there.
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
Do we go crunchy-cool
or golden Classic?
I know.
One for me and
one for you.
Now that's a sandwich!
Lay's.
Make Life Flavorful.
(announcer)
Welcome back.
Before the break,
the exes found out
that they all had power
for tomorrow's elimination,
which is bad news for some
of our misbehaved singles.
(Morgan)
You know, I tried so hard
■■■■
in this house
to be positive and happy.
'Cause the last thing
I wanted to do
was come in this house
and lose myself.
And now I feel so lost.
I know I don't have a say
with the exes,
but I want Corey out
before Farrah.
To me, he doesn't
contribute anything.
He has the personality
of a (bleep) pet rock.
And I feel like
Jay's pissed with you
just because, like--
Why would he be pissed
with me?
I feel like he's pissed
at you and her because--
Not at me.
She was kissing back.
It wasn't like a--
she said it was a snipe.
It wasn't a snipe.
It wasn't a snipe at all.
When you're in this house,
you kind of know
that evI mean, yeah,onna be
revshe could focus on Jay.,..■s
But honestly, like,
what's she gonna look at?
You know what I'm saying?
It's hard for me
to deal with the house
and all this
and me and you haven't
gotten anything,
like, resolved.
Resolved.
That (bleep) pisses me off
'cause it's like
I'm over here dying inside.
Darian knows that I do not allow
a man to not be accountable
fowrongdanise
thatt go it again.
Like, I need you to repent
to me like I'm Jesus.
When are you gonna fight
for me here
instead of involving yourself
in (bleep) that don't
(bleep) matter?
When the (bleep)
are you gonna fight for me?
You don't even know
what you want.
When we originally broke up,
she left me, literally.
But now I feel like she kind of
wants the best of both worlds.
The onlymatters
is me
can't strictly talk
about me and you right now,
then I will just go to bed.
That's fine.
Okay. Good-bye.
Like, this is (bleep).
That (bleep) again, man.
Let it go.
Are you good with us being done,
yes or no?
Of course not, Janelle.
I feel like we're still
up in the air.
It could go left,
it could go right.
At the end of the day,
Yeah,I'm my own man. know?
I'm gonna make my own decisions.
♪ One light ♪
♪ So co raise your head up
to the sky ♪
♪ Aye-aye-aye-aye ♪♪
We good now?
That is so cute.
(Farrah)
Look at you
and your cute breakfast.
■■■■ up!
and sausage.
So you haven't got sausage
in a while, so open up.
(both laughing)
(Sha)
That was a good one, huh?
Mmm.
Pretty good, huh?
It's tricky.
I really love it.
I'm just gonna go eat up
all my sausage.
See you later.
We both haven't got sausage
in a long time.
(Chad groans)
You know when you're
hung over
and you get ready
and you don't even
remember getting ready
but you just kind of come to
as you're looking good
and you're like, "Yeah"?
Yeah.
It's nice.
♪♪
It's so weird that an OG
might leave.
Might? Is.
So if I am really up
for elimination,
I'm not worried about it,
but I'm prepared,
and I'm G
a pantsuit tonight.
In all Farrah-ness,
I don't really feel like
I should be leaving.
Punted her straight
in the pooter.
I don't think I did.
What am I gonna do
to a girl's crotch?
The whole thing with Nazarian
or whatever her name is--
3v3v3va  Nazar-- N-Na--
Something with an N.
Just keep thinking her name
is like Nazarian.
It's like my plastic surgeon.
I really-- I'd rather be
thinking about that
than whatever she's about,
so...
What's up, gangsta?
What's going on?
Talk to me.
I'm just, like,
drained emotionally.
I just didn't wanna get
to that point yesterday
and I did,
and now I feel like
I, like, can't be myself.
What do you want
with us?
I don't know.
You don't trust me anymore.
It's like--
You honestly believe
that I don't trust you
at all?
I don't know.
(sighs)
I just wish you were
more honest with me.
I would prefer the truth.
Not 10%, 50%, 90%.
Give me the whole
damn thing.
Just wanna say sorry.
I didn't wanna put you
through all this.
Do I still want affection
and touch her all the time
and hug and (bleep)?
Hell yeah.
So I'll give her a shot.
I'll give her a chance again.
But...
I still care about you.
It's like, are you happier
with me here?
Yeah, what are they gonna do?
Send me a new blond?
(announcer)
We know where Jay stands,
but the rest of the exes
are still making up their minds.
I just wanna know where--
what-- like, where your
heads are at
and why you would--
you know, like,
who you guys wanna vote out
and, like, why?
(Diandra)
The only singles on the chopping
block are Corey and Farrah.
Corey because Morgan
wants him out.
She doesn't feel that she can
continue her relationship
ay while he's here.
And Farrah is
on the chopping block.
It's 'cause she kicked my girl
in the vagina and she needs
to (bleep) off.
Morgan's like,
"Someone help me, please."
But she's not actually
physically getting attacked,
and it's bull(bleep).
You know I get your side,
and I feel so bad for Morgan
that she's gotten bull(bleep)
after bull(bleep)
after bull(bleep).
But to be honest,
she did not get
this physically attacked.
That's so (bleep) up that any
of you guys are even deciding
for even the slightest
(bleep) bit.
Seriously?
I don't understand why people
wanna get Corey out.
Corey hasn't done anything.
Faa crazy,
delusional bitch.
■#■#     She's the one
that's the problem.
It's the craziest thing
you guy
We're supposed to be exes
and we're supposed
to stick together, correct?
Correct, and none
of you guys had my back.
It's the biggest
bull(bleep) ever.
Even though I know
she hurt you,
and, like, Farrah did
do things wrong,
everyone's done
a couple things wrong,
and at this point, like,
it's like we're not all
gonna come to one.
I think we should all just vote
what we think at this point.
So I'm just gonna go ahead
and crush Farrah just because
I feel like Farrah,
if you're gonna respect her,
she'll respectight back.
She treats all of us pretty good
other than the people
that she doesn't like,
which is everyone
for the most part.
I shouldn't have to (bleep)--
this should be easy.
It shouldn't
even be a question.
I totally understand why
you want her out.
I wish y'all would just
talk it out.
But you don't even
wanna talk to me, so...
I thought she did try
to talk to her.
She did try
to talk to Farrah,
and Farrah just blew--
I already know
I'm the bigger person.
I don't need to.
I'm not going up
to the bitch again.
And yes, I will
call her a bitch
'cause she's a bitch.
Like, I really don't care.
(Nurys)
It sucks to see that people
don't have my back.
I haven't done anything
to deserve that.
(sobbing)
HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN'T GET
HIGH SPEED INTERNET WHERE YOU
LIVE? WELL@>N WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITE INTERNET WHEREVER YOU
LIVE. HUGHESNET GEN 5 IS FAST.
YOU'LL GET 25MBPS, PLUS BUILT IN
WIFI, AND THERE'S NO HARD DATA
LIMITS. SO, WHEREVER YOU LIVE,
NONN DO MORE OF
EVERYTHING YOU LOVE ONLINE.
CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, STAY
INFORMED, WATCH THE LATEST
VIDEOS, AND HELP YOUR KIDS GET■
AMERICA'S NUMBER ONE CHOICE FOR
SATELLITE INTERNET. ACT NOW TO
SAVE $99 INSTANTLY WITH OUR
LIMITED TIME OFFER AND GET FREE
STANDARD INSTALLATION TOO. SO,
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR? GET
HUGHESNET GEN5. TO ORDER, CALL
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN. BE
SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR HOME PHONE
SERVICE, TOO. CALL THE NUMBER ON
This is Dell Cinema technology
with CinemaStream for
less buffering,
CinemaSound for
brilliant clarity,
Shop the biggest
Presidents Day ever
at Dell.com.
♪
At last, one red that works on
everyone.
New Made for All lip color from
Maybelline New York.
Tested on 50 skin tones.
New Made for All.l. ■J■J■J
Only from Maybelline New York.
You can't put a price on love.
■2■2
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
♪♪
Today is the day that the exes
finally have the power.
Now the singles get a taste
their own medicine.
One of you mother(bleep)
is going home.
■You're gone,
Well, I'm just gonna go ahead
and crush Farrah
just because I'm cool with her
and I'm just gonna go ahead
and not even deal
with the whole Corey thi
jusso■■cauwith aloodl with her
and I'm just gonna go ahead
■
I respe(sighs)
♪♪
Tonight, I am cutting Corey
because I think
that he came here
with a mission to stir up
feelings with Morgan.
I think that's
kind of passed, so...
♪♪
(Corey)
Honestly, I think that people
are, like, trying
to protect Morgan,
but she's, like, you know,
a little bitter at this point,
I think, and she, like, wants
to get me out now.
(Farrah)
I'm shocked that I would even be
up to be eliminated, really.
?         But as I am,
I'm ready to defend myself.
I'm here to stay.
What up?
What up, everybody?
Looking good.
(applause)
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■)
Now, before we get started,
I want to say something.
There's any more confrontations
that get physical,Beach."
you will be sent home.
We're all about love
here, baby.
All right, let's get down
to business.
Singles, we're gon' do things
a little bit differently
tonight.
Earlier today, the exes voted
for which single they wanted
to crush or cut.
■&■2■&■2■&■2■&■2■&■2■&■2■&■2■&■■
The sing■Treceived
ll be se
Crush votes, like y'all know,
cancels out cut votes.
And if the vote
results in a tie,
the power will revert
to the remaining singles.
■■■nd new l■   rekindle with a,
or just say (bleep) love.
By the end of your time here,
we're gonna put you through
the ultimate test.
I've tried real hard to campaign
to get Corey out of this house.
Be able to a!■
Before we get to these votes,c.
anybody wanna say anything?
I would like to make a speech.
Wow. Okay.
(Romeo)
A speech.
(Farrah)
Yeah.
So it's a "keep Farrah"
campaign.
But does she forget
we already voted?
If I, Farrah,
am here to stay,
I pledge unlimited
grocery shopping,
live-in maid.
Also lots more toilet paper,
cleaner, and air spray.
We gotta wrap it up
in a second.
Okay, all right.
All who voted for me
to be eliminated
will be on trash duty
and be shunned.
■Aaa■■
(laughter)
Honestly, in my heart of hearts,
I don't want either Farrah
or Corey to go.
Farrah, we gotta take
a seat right there.
Thank you.
All right.
(cheers and applause)
Whoo!
Thank you.
(giggling)
So funny.
All right, all right,
we gon' get back to it.
Let's get started.
Jozea.
■C■C■C
You already know what it is.
You good.
Nothing's in there.
No cut or no crush.
Yes.
You are safe, Jozea.
Maya, Malcolm,
Nicole, Cheyenne, Chad...
■t have nothing
in your pineapple.
(applause)
Which means you are safe.
We will got a lot of chips
still out there.
♪♪
With that being said,
Morgan,
please step up
to your pineapple.
♪♪
So how would you like
the vogo tonight?
I honestly would like Corey
to go home.
It's nothing against him,
but I have three exes
in the house.
Three is enough.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
You got a chip.
But it's a crush.
lause)
Duh.        But it's a crush.
Have a seat.
So, Janelle,
you've been in the middle
of a■8drama this week.
Mm-hmm.
Why don't you step up
to your pineapple?
Sure thing.
See how this goes.
♪♪
(laughter)
Think you have  a?
Maybe.
You never know.
Let's get to it.
Hold on.
You got a chip.
But it's a crush.
(applause)
Wow!
I said actions, people.
I said actions.
You got a crush,
which is a sign of love.
(bleep).
You better crush all this.
You are safe.
Have a sanelle.
I'm just saying.
Look at smile, man.
You see that?
Changes everything.
He's trying
to get his (bleep).
We finally got a chip.
YeahThank you.y is.
(Nelson)
Hey, Romeo.
I don't think he's the one
that put that crush vote
in there.
(all exclaiming)
Oh, (bleep).
Oh, (bleep)!
ç,
When Taco Bell's
Nacho Fries disappear...
Where did you go?
...one man must bring them back.
♪
♪Daddy's gonna bring
you Nacho Fries... ♪
Now Serving.
[BONG]
♪ ♪
Let's face it,
the world
could use some warmth.
♪ ♪
Juicy, sizzling steak.
Hand-tossed original dough.
Fresh cut onions,
crunchy green peppers,
a delicious
four cheese blend,
and our creamy Philly sauce.
All on the best
Philly Cheesesteak
you can get on a pizza.
Right now get
the new Philly
or any large specialty
Papa John's pizza
for just 12 bucks.
Hy-a-luronic Acid
Hyaluronic acid.
It's the skincare ingredient
that everyone is searching for!
And It's in here.
New from Revitalift:
Derm Intensives Hyaluronic
Acid Serum
With our highest concentration
of Hyaluronic Acid in a serum
Visibly plumps skin in
just one week
bounce back!
And reduces wrinkles for
younger-looking skin.
Powerful results
Validated by a panel
of dermatologists
New Revitalift Derm Intensives
Hyaluronic Acid Serum
From L'Oreal Paris
We're worth it.
Look! It's a Beluga whale.
Hmm...
I don't know.
That's it.
Suit up!
♪
Ha-ha! Watch the fur!
Look!
♪
ahhh...
Can we keep him?
What do you see in
your Cheetos?
On tour, every second counts.
I need great without the wait.
New Elvive
Rapid Reviver
Deep Conditioners.
L'Oréal's patented conditioners
work fast with no leave-in time.
Enriched with
damage-repairing serum.
2x easier detangling
2x less breakage
than with a leading conditioner.
Works deep. Repairs damage fast.
Hair's transformed instantly.
New Rapid Reviver
Deep Conditioners.
Elvive revives damaged hair.
We're worth it.
♪♪
♪ And everywhere I go ♪
♪ There's always
something to remind me ♪
♪ Of another
place and time ♪
♪♪
Hey, Romeo, Of another
I don't think he's the one
that put that crush vote
in there.
Oh.
I did.
(all exclaiming)
Oh, (bleep).
Wow.
Winning!
So you gave
the crush vote
to Janelle?
■@
Yes, I did.
What I respect about her
is that she apologized
ra.
I could not do anything
but respect that,
so■2
■
I gave you that crush vote.
is that she apologized
ra.        (applause)
Darian ain't getting
his (bleep).
I am pissed because Darian was
going to fully take the credit
for that crush, but instead
of wasting it on someone
that you barely even know,
it's like, put it towards me
to show me that, like,
you care.
Corey, please step up
to your pineapple.
If I had to guess,
you got some chips
in there.
Yeah.
Let's get to it.
First chip, cut.
Got another chip...
which is a cut.
You got two cut votes,
which means you're on
the hot seat.
Take a seat.
I might be going home because
of, like, her messiness,
and it's just not
that I would have to
potentially go home.
It'd be stupid for them
to kick me out of the house
'cause I never cause drama.
Like, I'm here to date,
you know, maybe find love.
So, next, Farrah.
Please step up
to your pineapple.
You think you have
I mean, I hope I havesh votes,
some crush votes. cut votes?■
All right, you ready
to get to it?
Yeah.
First one.
I'm so over Farrah!
You're giving everybody
a hard time.
You are a (bleep) person
to everybody.
You kicked one
of my closest friends
he house in her vagina.
You need to get
the (bleep) out.
(announcer)
Previously on "Ex on the Beach,"
ten incredibly single
and available reality stars
1#1#■#1#1#1#1#1#1#1#1#
are looking for love
while living with their exes.
Jozea and his ex Rob had an
emotional reunion at the beach.
Are you about to cry?
Aww!
(announcer)
Farrah wouldn't let
Nurys and Darian
have a private conversation.
I don't know why the (bleep)
you're coming out here.
(announcer)
So Farrah kicked her
in the privates.
Anto vote out Farrahet
in the flipped elimination
when the exes got the power
to vote out one of the singles.
after trying to get in the way
Coreof Morgan and Jay's seat■
relationship.
So now him and Farrah are both
in fear of elimination,
and one of them is going home.
♪♪
(thunder rumbling)
♪ Who knew that
the devil wore red? ♪
♪ Silk dress, yeah,
she always is a mess ♪
♪ She more petty
than the rest ♪
♪ Heartbreaker... ♪♪
(announcer)
Welcome back.
It's elimination night,
and this time, the exes are<<e
by giving them
a crush vote or a cut vote.
Nelson put his crush
in Janelle's pineapple
as a way to thank her
for taking the high road
after her fight with Diandra.
Darian tried to take credit
for it until he got called out.
OF, EY DIDN'T OWN ANYTHING,
THEY WEREN'T
WEALTHY LANDOWNERS,
THEY DIDN'T HAVE PROPERTIES
OR ANYTHING AT STAKE IN CUBA,
AND THEY HAD AN OPPORTUNITY TO
GO JUST AN HOUR NORTH AND THEN
GET A BETTER LIFE UH, FOR
THEMSELVES AND THEIR FAMILY,
VERY TYPICAL THING THAT
DREW PEOPLE HERE FOREVER.
GATES: THAT'S A BIG
HOUR THOUGH, MAN.
RUBIO: IT IS.
IT'S A BIG JUMP AND I'M
SURE THOSE EARLY YEARS WERE,
WERE DIFFICULT FOR THEM.
GATES: MARCO'S PARENTS
STRUGGLED MIGHTILY TO MAKE IT
IN AMERICA, MOVING FROM NEW
YORK TO MIAMI TO LAS VEGAS,
WORKING IN CASINOS AND HOTELS.
IT WAS AN IMMENSE EFFORT.
BUT EVEN SO, THE COUPLE TOOK
GREAT CARE TO MAKE SURE THAT
THEIR CHILDREN DIDN'T
SEE THEIR EXPERIENCE
AS A LIABILITY.
RUBIO: I NEVER REMEMBER
GROWING UP FEELING LIKE
I WAS LIMITED BECAUSE MY
DAD WAS A BARTENDER AND
MY MOM WORKED AS A MAID
AT THE IMPERIAL PALACE.
SOMEHOW THEY WERE ABLE TO
INSTILL IN US THE BELIEF THAT
THERE WAS NOBODY WE
SAW ON TELEVISION THAT
WE COULDN'T BE ONE DAY.
GATES: THAT'S FABULOUS.
MY PARENTS WERE THE SAME WAY.
THERE WAS NOTHING THAT
WE COULD ASPIRE TO THAT
WE COULD NOT ACHIEVE.
RUBIO: YEAH.
GATES: NOTHING.
RUBIO: THAT'S A REAL GIFT.
GATES: BUT WHERE DO YOU THINK
IT CAME FROM IN YOUR CASE?
RUBIO: I DON'T KNOW, UM.
GATES: I MEAN IT'S KINDA
CRAZY WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
RUBIO: WELL I THINK IT WAS
JUST KIND OF THE POINT OF
MY PARENTS' LIFE.
THEY TRIED A LOT OF
DIFFERENT THINGS,
AND I THINK THEIR FEELING WAS
WE WOULD HAVE THE CHANCE TO DO
THINGS THEY NEVER
HAD A CHANCE TO DO,
BUT INTERESTINGLY ENOUGH,
THEY NEVER HAD A SPECIFIC
DREAM FOR US, THEY JUST
WANTED US TO HAVE A DREAM,
WHATEVER THAT WAS,
AND KINDA PURSUE IT.
GATES: MARCO, OF COURSE,
DID INDEED FIND HIS OWN
DREAMS TO PURSUE.
AFTER GRADUATING FROM THE
UNIVERSITY OF MIAMI LAW SCHOOL,
HE ENTERED POLITICS,
RISING TO BECOME
ONE OF ONLY A HANDFUL OF
LATINOS IN THE U.S. SENATE.
LOOKING BACK, HE REMAINS
INTENSELY GRATEFUL TO HIS
PARENTS, AND SEES HIS SUCCESS
AS A VALIDATION OF THE CHOICE
THEY MADE IN IMMIGRATING,
AND OF THE NATION THEY
CHOSE AS THEIR NEW HOME.
RUBIO: AMERICA IS THIS ONE
PLACE WHERE YOU SAID TO PEOPLE
ALL OVER THE WORLD UH, MAYBE
YOU LIVE SOMEWHERE WHERE THEY
WON'T LET YOU BE WHO YOU
KNOW YOU CAN BE BECAUSE
YOUR FAMILY ISN'T
THE RIGHT PEOPLE.
BUT HERE IT DOESN'T MATTER,
HERE WE'RE GONNA JUDGE YOU BY
HOW HARD YOU'RE WILLING TO
WORK NOT ON WHAT YOUR LAST
NAME IS OR WHERE, WHAT
YOUR GREAT-GRANDFATHER DID.
GATES: MY THIRD GUEST IS
HAWAIIAN CONGRESSWOMAN
TULSI GABBARD.
GABBARD: ALOHA.
GATES: A RISING STAR
ON THE NATIONAL STAGE.
TULSI COMES FROM A
MILITARY FAMILY,
AND FOLLOWED THAT
SAME PATH HERSELF.
SHE JOINED THE ARMY
NATIONAL GUARD IN 2003,
WHEN SHE WAS 22 YEARS OLD.
THE NEXT YEAR, THE MAJORITY
OF HER UNIT WAS SELECTED FOR
SERVICE IN IRAQ,
BUT TULSI WASN'T,
SO SHE MADE A BOLD DECISION.
GABBARD: I KNEW VERY QUICKLY
THAT THERE WAS NO WAY THAT I
COULD STAY BACK IN
BEAUTIFUL HAWAII AS YOU KNOW,
MY FRIENDS AND BROTHERS AND
SISTERS IN UNIFORM DEPLOYED.
GATES: SO YOU VOLUNTEERED.
GABBARD: SO I VOLUNTEERED.
I CALLED MY
COMMANDER AND I TOLD HIM.
I HAVE TO GO WITH YOU GUYS.
AND, AND HE SAID,
NO, YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
AND IT TOOK A FEW
CONVERSATIONS FOR ME TO GET
HIM TO UNDERSTAND THAT I
WAS NOT GOING TO STAY HOME.
GATES: TULSI WAS SENT TO
A BASE IN IRAQ NICKNAMED
"MORTARITAVILLE" DUE TO
FREQUENT ENEMY ATTACKS.
SHE SERVED IN A
FIELD MEDICAL UNIT,
OBSERVING CASUALTIES AND
INJURIES ON A NEAR DAILY
BASIS, CONFRONTING FIRSTHAND
THE REALITIES OF WAR.
GABBARD: IT REALLY SHOWS YOU
WHAT'S IMPORTANT IN LIFE AND,
UM, THE SMALL
THINGS FALL AWAY.
GATES: YEAH.
GABBARD: WE HAD A BIG SIGN IN
OUR CAMP RIGHT ON ONE OF THE
GATES WHERE THE
PATROLS WENT IN AND OUT,
BIG BLACK LETTERS.
IT SAID: "IS TODAY THE DAY?"
GATES: WOW.
GABBARD: AND IT WAS AN
EVER-PRESENT REMINDER OF HOW
FRAGILE LIFE IS AND THAT OUR
TIME COULD COME AT ANY MOMENT,
SO MAKE IT COUNT.
DON'T TAKE
ANYTHING FOR GRANTED.
GATES: TULSI TOLD ME THAT HER
SERVICE WAS A MAJOR MOTIVATION
IN HER DECISION TO
RUN FOR CONGRESS,
DRIVING HER TO RECONSIDER
AMERICA'S MILITARY POLICIES
IN TERMS OF THEIR IMPACT
ON SOLDIERS AND CIVILIANS.
GABBARD: WHAT WILL
THE COST OF THIS BE,
DEVASTATION TO THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE,
TO THE WORLD, AND
WHAT, FOR WHAT?
GATES: A NOTION THAT TRULY HIT
HOME WHEN SHE RETURNED TO HER
FAMILY, AND SAW HOW POWERFULLY
HER ABSENCE HAD AFFECTED THEM.
GABBARD: WHEN I CAME HOME
FROM MY FIRST DEPLOYMENT.
WE PROBABLY LANDED AT
3 OR 4 IN THE MORNING.
WE SAW THE SUN RISING AS
WE WERE MARCHING INTO UM,
THIS HUGE HANGAR WHERE
ALL OF OUR FAMILIES
WERE GATHERED.
AND AS SOON AS THE GENERAL
SAID THAT WE WERE DISMISSED,
UH I RAN TO MY FAMILY AND MY
DAD WAS THE FIRST ONE THAT I
HUGGED AND UM, HE WAS SOBBING.
I DIDN'T, I DIDN'T
KNOW HOW, YOU KNOW,
I WAS SO FOCUSED IN MY WORLD
AND WHAT I WAS DOING I DIDN'T
FULLY REALIZE UNTIL THAT
MOMENT HOW ANXIOUS AND
STRESSED AND
WORRIED THEY WERE.
GATES: AFTER SPENDING
TIME WITH MY GUESTS,
I WAS STRUCK THAT
EACH HAD BEEN MOLDED
AND MOTIVATED BY ADVERSITY.
AS I DUG INTO THEIR ROOTS, I
FOUND THAT THEIR FAMILY TREES
WERE FILLED WITH PEOPLE
WHO SHARED THAT TRAIT.
BUT THEIR STORIES HAD
LARGELY BEEN FORGOTTEN.
IT WAS TIME TO UNEARTH THEM.
I STARTED WITH PAUL RYAN.
AS HIS NAME SUGGESTS, HIS
FATHER'S FAMILY IS IRISH,
AND PAUL IS WELL-VERSED
IN THEIR EXPERIENCE.
HE'S EVEN VISITED THE
TOWNS IN IRELAND WHERE
THE RYANS ONCE LIVED.
HIS MOTHER'S ROOTS, HOWEVER,
ARE A DIFFERENT MATTER.
HE KNOWS THAT SOME OF
HER ANCESTORS WERE GERMAN,
BUT LITTLE MORE.
SO WE BEGAN WITH HIS
MATERNAL GRANDFATHER,
WHOM PAUL LOVED, AND WHOSE
NAME WAS PARTICULARLY GERMAN.
THAT'S DR. ADOLPH HUTTER.
RYAN: MHMM. CAN YOU IMAGINE
HIS NAME WAS ADOLPH HUTTER?
GATES: I KNOW.
WOW. THAT'S...
RYAN: HE WAS IN THE US
NAVY IN WORLD WAR II.
GATES: THAT'S TOUGH.
RYAN: YEAH.
GATES: AND YOU'VE WRITTEN
THAT GROWING UP YOUR
GREATEST ASPIRATION WAS TO
BE LIKE DR. ADOLPH HUTTER.
RYAN: YEAH.
GATES: TELL ME ABOUT THAT.
RYAN: I ADORED THE MAN.
UGH, HE, HE, LIKE MY MOM,
HE WAS A REALLY CHIPPER,
HAPPY, FUNNY GUY,
VERY SMART, UM, WARM.
PEOPLE LIKED
BEING AROUND HIM, UM,
I JUST ADORED HIM.
GATES: PAUL HAD BEEN
TOLD BY HIS RELATIVES
THAT THE HUTTER FAMILY
ORIGINALLY IMMIGRATED TO
THE UNITED STATES
FROM BAVARIA.
BUT HE DIDN'T
KNOW WHEN THEY CAME,
OR ANYTHING AT ALL ABOUT
THE DETAILS OF THEIR JOURNEY.
WE FOUND THE
ANSWERS IN A PAMPHLET,
WRITTEN BUT NEVER PUBLISHED
BY ADOLPH'S GRANDFATHER,
A MAN NAMED JOSEPH HUTTER.
RYAN: "I WAS BORN JUNE 17,
1848 IN GERMANY AND IN 1854
WE CAME TO AMERICA.
I HAD NO IDEA THEY
CAME THAT EARLY.
IN 1854, WE CAME TO AMERICA
STOPPING AT HAVERSTRAW,
NEW YORK STATE UNTIL 1855."
GATES: HAVERSTRAW IS
ABOUT 40 MILES NORTH OF
NEW YORK CITY, BY THE WAY.
RYAN: OH OKAY.
NEVER HEARD OF IT.
"WE TRAVELED BY
RAIL TO MILWAUKEE.
WE WERE PENNILESS, AND
IN ORDER TO CONTINUE OUR
TRAVEL TO MADISON BY RAIL,
WE HAD TO PLEDGE ALL OF
OUR PERSONAL BELONGINGS,
SUCH AS BEDDING, ETCETERA,
FOR WHICH WE RECEIVED $12,
AND THIS TOOK US TO
MADISON, WISCONSIN."
THAT'S AN IMMIGRANT
STORY IF THERE EVER WAS ONE.
MAN, THAT'S A GREAT STORY.
I LOVE THAT STORY.
GATES: HAPPILY FOR PAUL,
HIS ANCESTOR'S STORY WAS
ABOUT TO GET EVEN BETTER.
ACCORDING TO JOSEPH, THE
HUTTERS CAME TO WISCONSIN TO
SETTLE IN SAUK COUNTY, WHERE
THERE WAS A GROWING COMMUNITY
OF GERMAN IMMIGRANTS.
BUT BY THE TIME
THEY REACHED MADISON,
THEY WERE
PENNILESS ONCE AGAIN,
AND SAUK COUNTY WAS
OVER 50 MILES AWAY!
THEY HAD NOTHING LEFT TO
SELL, SO THEY CONTINUED
THEIR JOURNEY, ON FOOT.
JOSEPH WAS ONLY SIX
YEARS OLD AT THE TIME.
RYAN: THEY WALKED 50 MILES.
GATES: YEAH 50 MILES.
THEY HAD NO MONEY.
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
RYAN: NO.
GATES: AND IF WE DO THE MATH,
JOSEPH'S MOTHER WAS LIKELY
PREGNANT WHEN THE FAMILY
IMMIGRATED AND WHEN THE FAMILY
WAS MAKING THAT 50
MILE WALK TO SAUK COUNTY.
CAN YOU IMAGINE THAT?
TALK ABOUT TOUGH.
RYAN: WOW, WOW.
PREGNANT WALKING 50 MILES
TO PLAIN, WISCONSIN
FROM MADISON.
IT'S A PRETTY HILLY AREA TOO.
I KNOW THAT SPOT. WOW.
GATES: WE NOW
TURNED TO THE ARCHIVES,
TO COMPARE JOSEPH'S ACCOUNT
WITH THE HISTORICAL RECORD.
THE 1860 CENSUS SHOWED JOSEPH
AS AN 11-YEAR-OLD BOY LIVING
ON THE SOUTH EDGE OF SAUK
COUNTY WITH HIS PARENTS:
JOHN AND BARBARA HUTTER.
THEY ARE YOUR THIRD
GREAT-GRANDPARENTS.
RYAN: DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THAT.
DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THEIR NAMES.
WOW. THAT'S REALLY SOMETHING.
GATES: NOW I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU SOMETHING REALLY COOL.
COULD YOU PLEASE
TURN THE PAGE?
RYAN: ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
GATES: SOMETHING YOU
NEVER DREAMED YOU'D SEE
IN YOUR WHOLE LIFE.
PAUL, YOU'RE LOOKING
AT THE PASSENGER LIST,
RYAN: OH REALLY?
GATES: FOR A SHIP
CALLED THE "CAESAR",
IT ARRIVED AT THE PORT OF
NEW YORK ON JUNE 20, 1854.
RYAN: HOW THE HECK.
HOW DO YOU GUYS
GET THIS STUFF?
HOW DO YOU DO THAT?
GATES: WOULD YOU PLEASE
READ WHO WAS ON THAT SHIP.
RYAN: THERE YOU
HAVE IT RIGHT THERE.
"JOHANNES HUTTER, 42,
FARMER, BARBARA, 42,
MICHAEL, 9, JOSEPH, 5."
GATES: YOU ARE LOOKING AT
THE RECORD OF THE MOMENT
THAT YOUR ANCESTORS
FIRST STEPPED FOOT IN
THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA.
RYAN: WOW. WOW.
THE "CAESAR"
PASSENGER MANIFEST.
GATES: MM-HMM.
RYAN: THAT'S AMAZING.
GATES: THE HUTTERS ARRIVED IN
AMERICA WITH NO MONEY AND NO
CONNECTIONS, AND FOUND
THEMSELVES NEAR THE BOTTOM
OF THE ECONOMIC LADDER.
BUT THEY DIDN'T
STAY THERE FOR LONG.
PAUL'S GREAT-GREAT GRANDFATHER
JOSEPH WOULD RISE UP,
WORKING FOR A BRICK MASON
BEFORE FOUNDING HIS OWN
CONSTRUCTION BUSINESS, AND
ASSURING HIS FAMILY'S SUCCESS.
RYAN: WOW.
GATES: WHAT'S IT
LIKE TO SEE THAT?
RYAN: I THINK IT'S
A BEAUTIFUL STORY.
I JUST LIKE THE FACT
THAT I'M A PART OF THE
WOVEN FABRIC OF THE COUNTRY.
I THINK THAT'S JUST
REALLY INTERESTING.
I THINK IT'S
GATES: YEAH, YEAH ME TOO.
RYAN: IT'S NEAT TO SEE WHAT
PEOPLE DO TO MAKE A BETTER
LIFE FOR THEMSELVES AND HOW
HARD IT WAS TO GET GOING IN
THIS COUNTY, TO
GET THINGS STARTED.
GATES: YEAH AND THEY
RISKED EVERYTHING.
RYAN: EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING.
GATES: AND THEY WERE
JUST GLAD TO BE HERE.
RYAN: THEY WALKED 50 MILES.
GATES: AND THEY
WALKED 50 MILES, YEAH.
RYAN: WHAT ARE THEY DOING,
HOW DID THEY DO THAT?
YEAH. IT'S NEAT.
GATES: IT'S INCREDIBLE.
RYAN: YEAH IT
REALLY IS, IT REALLY IS.
GATES: UNLIKE PAUL,
MARCO RUBIO KNOWS THE
IMMIGRANTS IN HIS FAMILY TREE.
THEY'RE HIS PARENTS, WHO
CAME TO THE UNITED STATES
FROM CUBA IN 1956.
BUT MARCO'S DEEPER ROOTS
WERE LARGELY A MYSTERY TO HIM.
AND AS WE BEGAN OUR RESEARCH,
WE SOON UNDERSTOOD WHY.
HIS FATHER, MARIO RUBIO REINA,
LOST BOTH OF HIS PARENTS BY
THE TIME HE WAS A TEENAGER,
AND ENDED UP LIVING ON THE
STREETS OF HAVANA.
A TRAUMA SO DEEP, IT
WAS RARELY DISCUSSED.
RUBIO: I KNOW VERY
LITTLE ABOUT HIS UPBRINGING.
I KNOW HIS MOTHER DIED
WHEN HE WAS VERY YOUNG OF
TUBERCULOSIS OR
SOME LUNG DISEASE.
AND THEN UH, HIS FATHER
AT SOME POINT REMARRIED,
AND UM, AND THEN,
WHEN HE WAS STILL
VERY YOUNG,
CERTAINLY BEFORE HE WAS 18,
HE MOVED OUT WITH ONE
OF HIS BROTHERS AND
LIVED SOMEWHERE ELSE.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS A GUY 14,
15 YEARS OF AGE ON HIS OWN.
GATES: AS IT TURNS OUT,
MARCO'S FATHER WASN'T THE
ONLY ONE IN HIS FAMILY TO
SUFFER SUCH LOSSES.
WE DISCOVERED THAT BOTH OF
MARIO'S PARENTS WERE ORPHANED
AT AN EARLY AGE, MEANING THAT
AT LEAST TWO GENERATIONS OF
MARCO'S ANCESTORS HAD TO FEND
FOR THEMSELVES AS CHILDREN.
RUBIO: YOU CAN BEGIN TO SEE
WHY SOME OF THESE STORIES WERE
NOT TOLD, ESPECIALLY THEY
DIDN'T HAVE, IF THEIR,
IF THESE KIDS WERE VERY
YOUNG WHEN THEIR PARENTS
DIED THEY JUST PROBABLY
DIDN'T KNOW AS MUCH ABOUT
THEIR PARENTS AND
COULDN'T PASS IT DOWN.
AND IT CERTAINLY
EXPLAINS A LOT ABOUT,
MY, MY FATHER
CERTAINLY WASN'T,
I DON'T THINK HE WAS ASHAMED
OF HIS FAMILY'S HISTORY,
HE JUST WASN'T A
PROMINENT FEATURE.
YOU WOULD THINK HE
KIND OF, YOU KNOW,
JUST APPEARED ON THE EARTH ONE
DAY AND THERE WAS NOTHING THAT
CAME BEFORE IT OTHER
THAN VERY VAGUE NOTIONS.
GATES: AND WHO WANTS TO
REVISIT ALL THAT PAIN?
RUBIO: YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
GATES: THAT'S SAD.
RUBIO: IT IS.
GATES: I WANTED TO RECOVER THE
STORIES THAT MARCO'S FAMILY
HAD LOST AMIDST
ALL THIS TRAGEDY.
ONE STOOD OUT AS
ESPECIALLY MEANINGFUL.
IT CONCERNS HIS
THIRD GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
A MAN NAMED JOSE
DE REINA Y TOSTA,
WHO WAS BORN AROUND
1760 IN SEVILLE, SPAIN.
JOSE'S BIRTHPLACE
WAS NOT UNEXPECTED,
AS MANY CUBANS HAVE
SPANISH ANCESTRY,
BUT HIS OCCUPATION TOOK
BOTH OF US BY SURPRISE.
RECORDS SHOW THAT HE
RECEIVED A LAW DEGREE
FROM THE UNIVERSITY OF GRANADA.
RUBIO: OH WOW.
HE'S A LAWYER.
GATES: 1786.
RUBIO: SO MY GREAT-
GREAT GRANDFATHER,
MY THIRD GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
WAS A LAWYER?
GATES: HE GOT A LAW DEGREE
200 YEARS BEFORE YOU DID.
RUBIO: WOW. WELL,
WE WAITED LONG ENOUGH.
THAT'S UNREAL.
THAT'S REALLY AMAZING.
GATES: YOU THOUGHT YOU
WERE THE FIRST LAWYER.
RUBIO: I THOUGHT I WAS.
GATES: WRONG.
RUBIO: THE FIRST IN TWO
CENTURIES. BUT UH, WOW.
GATES: AND GUESS WHAT?
HE WENT ON TO BECOME
A PUBLIC PROSECUTOR.
IN THE YEAR 1793 HE WAS
ADMITTED TO THE ATTORNEYS
PROFESSIONAL GUILD IN SEVILLE,
AND HE WENT ON TO BECOME A
PUBLIC PROSECUTOR.
RUBIO: SO, THERE YOU GO.
WELL, IT'S THE FIRST TIME I
READ ANYWHERE THAT ANYBODY IN
MY FAMILY HAD ANYTHING TO DO
WITH GOVERNMENT UP UNTIL ME.
GATES: JOSE NEVER REACHED THE
HEIGHTS THAT HIS DESCENDENT
MARCO HAS REACHED, BUT HIS
CAREER IN GOVERNMENT WAS
MARKED BY ONE
INCREDIBLE ACCOMPLISHMENT.
IN THE EARLY 1830S, JOSE
WAS SERVING IN MURCIA,
A PROVINCIAL CAPITAL,
WHEN A CHOLERA EPIDEMIC
STRUCK THE CITY.
AMIDST STAGGERING CASUALTIES,
JOSE FOUND HIMSELF THRUST INTO
THE SPOTLIGHT, COORDINATING
HEALTH AUTHORITIES,
THE POLICE, AND THE COURTS, AS
OTHER HIGH-RANKING OFFICIALS
DIED OR FLED.
RUBIO: SO HE WASN'T
JUST A GUY THAT WAS THERE,
PUNCHING THE CLOCK.
GATES: YOU'VE HAD TO
DEAL WITH HURRICANES.
RUBIO: YEAH?
GATES: CAN YOU RELATE
TO HIS HANDLING OF A
LARGE-SCALE CRISIS?
RUBIO: YEAH, EXCEPT THEY
DON'T HAVE THE RESOURCES
WE HAVE, YOU KNOW?
GATES: YEAH.
RUBIO: I MEAN JUST IMAGINING
HOW THIS THING WAS SPREADING,
PROBABLY HAD
PEOPLE CLOSE TO HIM.
THEY WERE LIVING THE
TRAGEDY ALONG WITH
HAVING TO ADMINISTER IT.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE YOU KNEW,
PEOPLE THAT WORKED FOR YOU ALL
OF A SUDDEN GOT SICK, SO YOUR
WORKFORCE WAS UNDER ATTACK.
IT MUST'VE BEEN AN EPIC CRISIS
AND VERY DIFFICULT TO HANDLE,
BUT HE COULD'VE
LEFT AND HE STAYED.
GATES: HOW'S
THAT MAKE YOU FEEL?
RUBIO: I GOT SOME
SHOES TO FILL, HUH?
GATES: JOSE
SURVIVED THE EPIDEMIC,
LIVING UNTIL HE WAS
ABOUT 70 YEARS OLD.
HIS SON, MARCO'S
GREAT-GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
ALSO TOOK UP GOVERNMENT WORK,
SERVING IN THE PAY CORPS OF
THE SPANISH ARMY.
SURVEYING THEIR LIVES,
MARCO WONDERED HOW THESE
ANCESTORS MAY HAVE
INFLUENCED HIM,
EVEN THOUGH THEIR
STORIES HAD BEEN LOST.
RUBIO: THOSE CAMPAIGNS
THAT I RAN MY DAD LOVED THEM,
I MEAN HE LOVED BEING INVOLVED
IN IT AND LOVED DOING IT.
I CAN'T IMAGINE HE
KNEW ANY OF THIS,
LIKE NO ONE'S EVER
TOLD US ANY OF THIS.
SO IT JUST KINDA
TELLS YOU THAT SOMEWHERE,
YOU KNOW, IN, IN THEIR BLOOD
BACK THEN IT WAS SOMEONE WHO
CARED ABOUT AND WAS INVOLVED
IN GOVERNMENT SERVICE AND,
AND THEN THERE WAS THESE
THINGS THAT MADE IT
IMPOSSIBLE FOR THREE
GENERATIONS TO DO IT,
AND THEN SUDDENLY YOU
PUT SOMEONE IN THE RIGHT
ENVIRONMENT AND THEY
WIND UP, YOU KNOW,
IN THE US SENATE.
THAT'S JUST UNBELIEVABLE.
GOD. WOW.
GATES: LIKE MARCO,
MY NEXT GUEST,
HAWAII'S TULSI GABBARD,
SEEMS TO HAVE INHERITED
A CALL TO SERVE.
INDEED, THE VERY REASON THAT
THE GABBARD FAMILY ENDED UP
IN THE PACIFIC AT ALL
LIES WITH THE MILITARY.
TULSI'S GREAT-GRANDFATHER, A
MAN NAMED BENJAMIN GABBARD,
CAME TO SAMOA AS A SAILOR
WITH THE U.S. NAVY.
AND WHILE ON LEAVE, HE
VISITED THE ISLAND OF APIA,
WHERE HE MET A LOCAL RESIDENT.
A WOMAN, NAMED CARRIE BARTLEY.
WE PICK UP THE COUPLE'S
STORY IN A 1920 EDITION OF
THE "SAMOA TIMES".
GABBARD: "A MAN-O'-WARSMAN
SPENT HIS WEEKEND AT APIA.
DURING HIS SHORT STAY HE WAS
MARRIED TO A SAMOAN BELLE,
THE BRIDE WAS
MISS CARRIE BARTLEY,
THE BRIDEGROOM,
MR. B.H. GABBARD,
WAS ATTENDED BY A
NUMBER OF HIS COMPANIONS
IN THE U.S. NAVY."
GATES: THAT'S YOUR
GREAT-GRANDPARENTS'
WEDDING ANNOUNCEMENT.
ISN'T THAT COOL?
GABBARD: THAT IS COOL.
"SAMOAN BELLE."
GATES: SAMOAN BELLE.
GABBARD: LITTLE DIFFERENT
THAN THE SOUTHERN BELLE.
GATES: INDEED.
THE NAVY WAS THE ONLY
REASON THAT HE WAS IN SAMOA,
WITHOUT IT YOU NEVER
WOULD HAVE BEEN BORN.
SO THANK GOD FOR THE NAVY.
GABBARD: YES.
GATES: TO TRACE THE ROOTS OF
TULSI'S GREAT-GRANDPARENTS,
WE FOUND OURSELVES
EXPLORING ARCHIVES
SCATTERED ACROSS THE GLOBE.
BENJAMIN'S ROOTS
STRETCH THROUGH KENTUCKY,
VIRGINIA AND
PENNSYLVANIA TO GERMANY!
CARRIE'S MOTHER
WAS A SAMOAN NATIVE,
WITH ANCESTORS WHO HAVE LIKELY
BEEN IN THE PACIFIC ISLANDS
FOR CENTURIES.
AND CARRIE'S FATHER, A
MAN NAMED CHARLES BARTLEY,
WAS BORN IN A PLACE
THAT TULSI HAD NEVER
ASSOCIATED WITH HER FAMILY.
WANT TO TAKE A WILD
GUESS WHERE WE FOUND HIM?
I'LL GIVE YOU A NICKEL.
GABBARD: I DON'T KNOW.
CALIFORNIA?
GATES: YOU LOSE.
GABBARD: I OWE YOU A NICKEL.
GATES: YOU OWE ME A NICKEL.
PLEASE TURN THE PAGE.
TULSI, ON THE RIGHT IS A BIRTH
REGISTER FROM THE YEAR 1858.
WOULD YOU PLEASE
READ THE TRANSCRIPTION?
SURPRISE.
GABBARD: "BIRTHS IN THE
DISTRICT OF AUCKLAND,
NEW ZEALAND.
GATES: TULSI, YOU HAVE
ROOTS IN NEW ZEALAND.
THIS IS WHERE YOUR
PEOPLE COME FROM.
DID YOU HAVE ANY IDEA?
GABBARD: NO. NO. WOW.
THIS IS REALLY COOL.
GATES: CHARLES
BARTLEY IS TULSI'S
GREAT-GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
AND HIS BIRTHPLACE POSED A
QUESTION: HOW DID SOMEONE BORN
IN NEW ZEALAND IN THE 1850S
END UP STARTING A FAMILY
IN SAMOA IN THE 1880S?
THE ANSWER LAY IN A
SAMOAN ENCYCLOPEDIA,
WHERE CHARLES' LIFE
SOUNDED LIKE THE PLOT
OF AN ADVENTURE NOVEL.
GABBARD: "MR. CHARLES BARTLEY,
STOREKEEPER AND TRADER,
OF SALANO, SAVAII, WAS
BORN IN AUCKLAND IN 1857,
BUT WAS EDUCATED IN APIA,
HAVING BEEN ONLY FIVE YEARS
OLD GONE WITH HIS
PARENTS TO SAMOA.
AT TEN YEARS OF AGE, HE
RAN AWAY TO SEA AND SPENT
12 YEARS IN A ROAMING LIFE."
GATES: WHAT A STORY!
ACCORDING TO
THIS ENCYCLOPEDIA,
YOUR FAMILY LEFT NEW ZEALAND
FOR SAMOA SOMETIME AROUND
1862, WHEN CHARLES
WAS FIVE YEARS OLD.
BUT CHARLES DIDN'T STAY
LONG IN HIS NEW HOME.
AS THIS TELLS US, AT THE
AGE OF TEN HE WENT TO SEA.
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
A TEN-YEAR-OLD ON A SHIP?
GABBARD: GOSH. NO.
GATES: HOW DO YOU THINK
STORIES LIKE THIS ARE LOST?
GABBARD: I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK THAT MY PARENTS
THEY'RE HUMBLE PEOPLE AND
I THINK SOMETIMES NOT
DOCUMENTING AND NOT TAKING
THE TIME TO FOCUS ON THIS
BECAUSE YOU'RE FOCUSING ON
WHAT'S RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU
STORIES LIKE THIS PROBABLY,
UM, FELL TO THE BACK.
GATES: WHAT'S YOUR DAD
GOING TO MAKE OF THIS STORY?
GABBARD: I THINK HE
WILL BE MIND-BLOWN.
GATES: WE CAN'T VERIFY THE
ENCYCLOPEDIA'S ACCOUNT OF
CHARLES' ROAMING YOUTH,
BUT WE DO KNOW THAT
HE DID, IN FACT, SETTLE
IN SAMOA AND THAT HE DID
INDEED BECOME A TRADER.
WE ALSO KNOW THAT AS AN ADULT,
CHARLES FACED A DAUNTING
CHALLENGE, ONE THAT WOULD HAVE
SPECIAL SIGNIFICANCE TO TULSI.
IN 1905, A SAMOAN
VOLCANO ERUPTED,
SENDING LAVA RUSHING STRAIGHT
TOWARDS CHARLES' DOOR.
GABBARD: "LAVA
SPREADS OVER ISLAND.
THE VOLCANO ON THE ISLAND
OF SAVAII IS STILL ACTIVE.
SOME PERSONS WILL NOT
LEAVE THEIR HOUSES UNTIL THE
DWELLINGS ARE ACTUALLY SET
ON FIRE BY THE BURNING LAVA.
THE LAVA HAS DESTROYED
ALL OF SALAGO, INCLUDING
THE HOME OF MR. BARTLEY,
A WELL-KNOWN RESIDENT."
GATES: CHARLES LOST HIS HOME.
GABBARD: GEEZ.
GATES: THIS ERUPTION WAS
HUGE INTERNATIONAL NEWS,
AND YOUR
GREAT-GREAT-GRANDFATHER
CHARLES WAS MENTIONED BY
NAME IN MANY ARTICLES,
IN MANY NEWSPAPERS.
IN FACT, A PHOTO OF HIS HOUSE
RIGHT BEFORE IT WAS DESTROYED
MADE IT INTO AN AUSTRALIAN
NEWSPAPER CALLED
"THE TOWN AND
COUNTRY JOURNAL."
THERE IT IS ON THE LEFT.
GABBARD: "MR. H. C.
BARTLEY'S HOUSE,
TAKEN AT 1 PM ON SATURDAY,
JANUARY 27, 1906.
LAVA CAN BE SEEN OVER
THE BUGGY IN THE DISTANCE,
SOME 60 YARDS AWAY.
THE HOUSE WAS BURNED AND STONE
COVERED HALFWAY UP THE WINDOWS
AT 11 O'CLOCK THE SAME NIGHT."
GATES: CAN YOU IMAGINE?
GABBARD: SADLY I CAN BECAUSE
WE ARE LITERALLY SEEING THIS
HAPPENING ON HAWAII ISLAND.
GATES: RIGHT NOW.
GABBARD: RIGHT NOW.
I WAS JUST THERE AND BOTH FLEW
OVER AND WALKED ON THE LAVA
THAT HAS BEEN SPOUTING.
GATES: WOW, THAT'S AMAZING.
GABBARD: AND IT'S JUST YEAH,
BEEN INCREDIBLE TO SEE HOW
COMPLETELY IT HAS
CHANGED EVERYTHING.
I MEAN HOUSES THAT I SAW,
FARMS THAT I SAW DURING THE
FIRST WEEK OF THE
ERUPTION NOW ARE,
IT'S LIKE THEY NEVER EXISTED.
GATES: THE VOLCANO ON CHARLES'
ISLAND CONTINUED TO ERUPT FOR
SIX YEARS, AND DESTROYED
MUCH OF WHAT HE OWNED.
BUT TULSI'S
ANCESTOR REFUSED TO FOLD .
GABBARD: "MR. BARTLEY IS THE
LARGEST LOSER BY THE PRESENT
VOLCANIC ERUPTION, HAVING
HAD HIS TWO STORES AND
CONTENTS BURNED, AND
HIS BOAT HAS ALSO GONE.
MR. BARTLEY, HOWEVER,
IS MADE OF STERN STUFF
AND IS NOT DISCOURAGED.
HE IS NOW PREPARING FOR
A FRESH START BEYOND THE
REACH OF THE PRESENT
VOLCANIC OUTBREAK."
GATES: STERN STUFF.
GABBARD: TRULY A TOUGH GUY.
GATES: YEAH. DOES THIS SOUND
LIKE ANYBODY IN YOUR FAMILY?
GABBARD: OH, YES.
GATES: PRETTY COOL.
GABBARD: YES.
THAT'S REALLY SPECIAL.
GATES: WE HAD ALREADY
TAKEN PAUL RYAN BACK TO HIS
GREAT-GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
JOSEPH HUTTER,
A GERMAN IMMIGRANT
WHO FOUNDED A
CONSTRUCTION BUSINESS
IN WISCONSIN.
NOW, WE WANTED TO GO FURTHER
ON THIS LINE, TO SEE WHERE
EXACTLY THE HUTTER
FAMILY ORIGINATED,
AND TRY TO LEARN WHY THEY
MADE THEIR JOURNEY TO AMERICA.
THESE ARE QUESTIONS THAT
HAVE LONG ANIMATED PAUL.
AS, GROWING UP, HIS
GERMAN ROOTS WERE NEVER AS
MUCH-DISCUSSED AS
HIS IRISH HERITAGE.
RYAN: I ALWAYS WONDERED
WHY THEY IMMIGRATED.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
BECAUSE I KNOW
THE FAMINE IRISH.
I KNOW THE IRISH STORY.
THAT'S A PRETTY
SIMPLE STORY, YOU KNOW.
GATES: YEAH, SURE.
RYAN: BUT I NEVER REALLY
KNEW THE BAVARIAN STORY,
BUT I DON'T KNOW IF
YOU KNOW THAT OR NOT.
YOU'RE GONNA GET THERE.
GATES: WAIT AND SEE.
RYAN: I HAVE NO CLUE.
I DON'T WHY.
GATES: TRACING PAUL'S FAMILY
IN GERMANY WOULD PROVE TO
BE A SUBSTANTIAL TASK.
WE KNEW THAT JOSEPH HUTTER
ARRIVED IN NEW YORK IN 1854,
BUT HIS ARRIVAL RECORD
DIDN'T NAME HIS HOMETOWN.
SO ALL WE HAD TO GO ON WAS A
FAMILY STORY THAT THE HUTTERS
ORIGINALLY CAME FROM BAVARIA.
FORTUNATELY, BAVARIAN CHURCHES
KEEP VERY GOOD RECORDS.
RYAN: JOHANNES HUTTER,
BORN JANUARY 6TH, 1812
IN HOCHABRUNN.
PARENTS: JOHANNES
HUTTER, WEAVER,
WEAVER IN HOCHABRUNN,
AND HIS WIFE MARGARETHA."
GATES: YOU'RE LOOKING AT
THE BAPTISMAL RECORD...
RYAN: HOW DO YOU
GUYS GET THIS STUFF?
GATES: FROM 1812 FOR YOUR
THIRD GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
YOUR GREAT-GREAT-
GREAT-GRANDFATHER'S
BAPTISMAL RECORD.
RYAN: HOW DID YOU GET THAT?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
GATES: AND JOHANNES OF
COURSE BECAME KNOWN AS JOHN.
RYAN: YEAH. MY GOSH.
GATES: WE NOW KNEW THAT
PAUL'S ANCESTORS CAME FROM
HOCHABRUNN, A VILLAGE ON
THE OUTSKIRTS OF THE TOWN OF
WALDMUCHEN IN EASTERN BAVARIA.
AND THIS ALLOWED US TO PROVIDE
SOME CONTEXT TO HIS FAMILY'S
DECISION TO EMIGRATE.
BY THE TIME THE
HUTTERS LEFT, IN 1854,
MOST OF HOCHABRUNN'S
POPULATION WERE TRADESPEOPLE
OR TENANT FARMERS,
EARNING A MEAGER LIVING,
OFTEN STRUGGLING
SIMPLY TO FEED THEMSELVES.
THEY LEFT LITTLE EVIDENCE
OF THEIR LIVES BEHIND,
BUT PAUL WAS THRILLED TO
SEE ANYTHING WE COULD FIND.
RYAN: "JOHANNES HUDERER.
BORN JANUARY 29,"
THAT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
GATES: OH, WOW.
RYAN: 1788 IN HOCHABRUNN.
"PARENTS: JOHANN", OH MY!
GATES: YEAH, JOHANN.
RYAN: "JOHANN ADAM HUDERER,
WEAVER IN HOCHABRUNN,
AND HIS WIFE BARBARA."
GATES: THIS IS ANOTHER
BAPTISMAL RECORD,
FOR YOUR FOURTH
GREAT-GRANDFATHER.
RYAN: FOURTH
GATES: YEAH, JOHANNES.
AND NOW...
RYAN: NOBODY IN MY ENTIRE
FAMILY KNOWS ANY OF THIS STUFF.
NOBODY KNOWS THIS STUFF.
GATES: WOW, THAT'S GREAT.
WELL YOU JUST MET ANOTHER
GENERATION OF YOUR FAMILY,
YOUR FIFTH GREAT-GRANDPARENTS,
HIS PARENTS JOHANN ADAM
HUDERER, ANOTHER WEAVER
AND HIS WIFE BARBARA,
BABL, JOHANN OR
ADAM AS HE WAS KNOWN,
WAS BORN APRIL 1,
READY FOR THIS?
1757 IN HOCHABRUNN.
RYAN: 1757.
GATES: 1757. THAT'S
18 YEARS BEFORE
THE BATTLES OF
CONCORD AND LEXINGTON.
RYAN: YEAH, RIGHT,
RIGHT. MY GOSH.
GATES: IT'S AMAZING.
WHAT'S IT LIKE TO
SEE THAT DOCUMENT?
RYAN: I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN'T, I NEVER, I DIDN'T
EXPECT YOU TO DO THIS.
WOW. THAT'S REALLY SOMETHING.
I DON'T REALLY
HAVE WORDS FOR THIS.
I'M AMAZED YOU
FOUND THIS STUFF.
GATES: YOU HAVE DEEP ROOTS IN
GERMANY AND WE DON'T KNOW FOR
SURE BUT WE THINK THEY CAME
FOR ECONOMIC OPPORTUNITY.
THAT'S THE ONLY
THING THAT MAKES SENSE.
RYAN: THAT'S MY GUESS,
I GUESS. I MEAN, YEAH...
GATES: LET ME
PUT IT THIS WAY..
RYAN: POOR FARMERS IN
BAVARIA AND THEY CAME FOR.
GATES: PEOPLE WITH A LOT
OF MONEY IN THE BANK
DON'T MIGRATE.
RYAN: YEAH. RIGHT,
RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
GATES: WE HAD ONE MORE
SURPRISE FOR PAUL:
A SECRET HIDDEN
WITHIN HIS OWN DNA.
WHEN WE ANALYZED
HIS ADMIXTURE,
WHICH REFLECTS HIS ANCESTRY
OVER ROUGHLY THE LAST
500 YEARS, WE DISCOVERED THAT
HIS HERITAGE WAS MORE VARIED
THAN THE PAPER
TRAIL HAD REVEALED.
COULD YOU READ YOUR
ADMIXTURE PERCENTAGES?
RYAN: OKAY.
61% IRISH/SCOTTISH/WELSH.
GATES: WHAT A SHOCK!
RYAN: WHAT A SHOCK!
61% IRISH.
15% SCANDINAVIAN,
9% EASTERN EUROPEAN,
3% ASHKENAZI JEWISH,
THAT'S REALLY COOL.
GATES: THAT IS A LOT.
RYAN: IS IT REALLY?
GATES: YEAH, THAT
MEANS SOMEWHERE,
THERE'S A JEWISH GUY THERE.
RYAN: THAT'S REALLY COOL.
YEAH, THERE'S A JEWISH
GUY IN THERE SOMEWHERE.
GATES: OR A WOMAN.
RYAN: YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
RIGHT! VERY COOL.
GATES: THREE PERCENTAGE POINTS
INDICATES THAT PAUL COULD HAVE
A THIRD GREAT-GRANDPARENT OF
FULL ASHKENAZI JEWISH DESCENT,
THOUGH IT IS ALSO POSSIBLE
THAT HE HAS MULTIPLE LINES
WITH MORE DISTANT
JEWISH ANCESTRY.
REGARDLESS, THE DNA
EVIDENCE IS UNEQUIVOCAL:
PAUL RYAN HAS JEWISH ROOTS.
A RESULT THAT HE WELCOMES,
AS A REFLECTION OF AMERICA'S
GREAT DIVERSITY.
RYAN: I THINK OF
THE MELTING POT.
I THINK OF THE FACT THAT YOU
CAN COME FROM ANY BACKGROUND
WHATSOEVER AND MAKE IT IN THIS
COUNTRY BECAUSE OF FREEDOM,
BECAUSE OF OUR SYSTEM,
BECAUSE OF PLURALISM.
GATES: IT'S WHO WE ARE.
IT'S PART OF OUR CULTURAL DNA.
RYAN: YEAH. I THINK
THAT'S FASCINATING.
GATES: YEAH, IT IS.
RYAN: IT IS.
GATES: WE'D ALREADY INTRODUCED
TULSI GABBARD TO HER
GREAT-GRANDFATHER BENJAMIN,
THE SAILOR WHO CAME TO SAMOA
WITH THE U.S. NAVY.
NOW, TURNING TO HER
MOTHER'S FAMILY TREE,
WE CAME UPON
ANOTHER MILITARY STORY,
FROM A VERY
DIFFERENT TIME AND PLACE.
TULSI'S THIRD
GREAT GRANDFATHER,
A MAN NAMED LEWIS PORTER,
GREW UP IN PENNSYLVANIA AS THE
UNITED STATES MOVED INEXORABLY
TOWARDS THE CIVIL WAR.
GATES: DID YOU HAVE ANY IDEA?
GABBARD: NO. NO.
I'VE, I'VE YOU KNOW, LOVED
READING ABOUT IT AND LEARNING
ABOUT IT AND YOU KNOW, WE'VE
GONE THROUGH GETTYSBURG
AND YOU KNOW, SEEN SOME OF
THE REENACTMENTS BUT I HAVE
NEVER IMAGINED THAT MY
ANCESTORS WERE THERE FOR THAT.
GATES: COULD YOU
PLEASE TURN THE PAGE?
NOW, YOU KNOW WHERE THE
NATIONAL ARCHIVES IS, RIGHT?
GABBARD: YES.
GATES: THIS IS A PAGE OF A
RECORD THAT WE FOUND IN THE
NATIONAL ARCHIVES.
WOULD YOU MIND READING
THE TRANSCRIBED SECTION?
GABBARD: "STATE OF OHIO,
TOWN OF WARREN.
I, LEWIS PORTER,
BORN IN PENNSYLVANIA,
AGE 40 YEARS, VOLUNTEERED THIS
31 DAY OF MARCH 1864 TO SERVE
AS A SOLDIER IN THE ARMY OF
THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA."
WOW!
GATES: YOUR GREAT-GREAT-
GREAT-GRANDFATHER
VOLUNTEERED TO FIGHT IN
THE UNION ARMY AGAINST THE
CONFEDERACY, HOW DOES
THAT MAKE YOU FEEL?
GABBARD: WOW. HONORED.
GATES: TULSI'S ANCESTOR
NOT ONLY VOLUNTEERED,
HE SERVED IN ONE OF THE
MOST SIGNIFICANT CAMPAIGNS
OF THE ENTIRE WAR.
IN THE SPRING OF 1864, JUST
WEEKS AFTER HE'D ENLISTED,
LEWIS PORTER'S REGIMENT SET
OFF UNDER GENERAL WILLIAM
TECUMSEH SHERMAN, ON HIS
FAMED ATLANTA CAMPAIGN.
WITH LITTLE TRAINING,
LEWIS SUDDENLY FOUND HIMSELF
MOVING SOUTH, STRAIGHT INTO THE
HEART OF THE CONFEDERACY.
NOW, YOU'VE SEEN COMBAT,
GABBARD: YEAH.
GATES: HOW DO YOU THINK
LEWIS MUST HAVE FELT?
GABBARD: OH, MY GOSH.
THIS IS A TOTALLY
DIFFERENT LEVEL I MEAN,
WHAT THEY, WHAT
THEY WENT THROUGH.
I ACTUALLY, AS PART OF MY
OFFICER CANDIDATE TRAINING,
IN ORDER TO EARN MY COMMISSION
AS A LIEUTENANT WE WENT AND
WALKED THROUGH THOSE
BATTLEFIELDS AND HEARD
ABOUT YOU KNOW, THE
TACTICS AND THE BATTLES
THAT WERE FOUGHT THERE.
GATES: AND IT NEVER OCCURRED
TO YOU THAT ONE OF YOUR
ANCESTORS COULD BE THERE.
GABBARD: GOSH, NO.
GATES: THAT'S AMAZING.
THAT IS AMAZING THAT
YOU'VE BEEN THERE.
GABBARD: IT WAS COOL JUST
TO BE THERE AND KIND OF
WALK THROUGH THOSE
FOOTSTEPS THAT THEY TOOK,
BUT UM, NO, I, THE THOUGHT
NEVER CROSSED MY MIND.
GATES: THE ATLANTA
CAMPAIGN WOULD PROVE
A SPECTACULAR SUCCESS.
BUT IT CAME AT A HEAVY COST.
THE UNION WAS OPPOSED BY
ONE OF THE LARGEST ARMIES
IN THE CONFEDERACY.
AND THE TWO FORCES SOON
FACED OFF AT A SMALL TOWN
IN NORTHERN GEORGIA
KNOWN AS RESACA.
FOR TWO DAYS, THE UNION
STRUGGLED TO DRIVE THE
CONFEDERATES FROM THE FIELD,
FIGHTING ON TERRAIN THAT WAS
ILL-SUITED FOR AN ATTACK.
LEWIS'S REGIMENT WAS
ON THE FRONT LINES.
WE FOUND A NEWSPAPER ARTICLE,
WRITTEN JUST WEEKS
AFTER THE BATTLE,
THAT DESCRIBES
WHAT THEY ENDURED.
GABBARD: "PORTIONS
OF PALMER'S CORPS,
IN ATTEMPTING TO
CHARGE THE REBELS IN FRONT,
WERE COMPELLED TO WADE
A CREEK WAIST DEEP, WHICH
RAN AT THE FOOT OF THE BLUFF;
AND THEN ACROSS A
VALLEY FILLED WITH DITCHES,
FULLY EXPOSED TO A FIRE
FROM THE REBEL WORKS.
NEVER DID MEN GO TO
WORK MORE GALLANTLY,
OR CONTEST MORE NOBLY; BUT
THEY COULD NOT ACCOMPLISH
IMPOSSIBILITIES, AND,
AFTER SEVERE LOSS,
WERE OBLIGED TO WITHDRAW."
GATES: COULD YOU IMAGINE?
GABBARD: IT'S TOUGH.
GATES: NOW, WE DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED TO LEWIS
IN THAT BATTLE, BUT HIS
REGIMENT WAS ASSAULTING THE
VERY SAME CENTER STRETCH
OF THE CONFEDERATE LINE
DESCRIBED IN THAT ARTICLE.
HE AND HIS COMRADES LIKELY
DESCENDED A STEEP RIDGE,
AND THEN CROSSED A CREEK
AND SCALED AN ALMOST VERTICAL
SLOPE WHERE THE CONFEDERATES
HAD DUG EARTHWORKS,
ALL THE WHILE EXPOSED
TO DIRECT ENEMY
ARTILLERY AND RIFLE FIRE.
GABBARD: JEEZ.
GATES: SO HE WAS OUT THERE.
I MEAN HE WAS EXPOSED.
HE WAS ON THE LINE.
DO YOU FEEL A SENSE
OF PRIDE? FOR YOUR...
GABBARD: I DO, I
REALLY DO. JUST...
GATES: KNOWING THAT THIS GUY
EXISTS ON YOUR FAMILY TREE?
GABBARD: ABSOLUTELY.
YOU KNOW?
IT SAYS A LOT ABOUT THIS
ETHIC OF SERVICE...
GATES: INDEED.
GABBARD: GOING BACK MUCH
FARTHER THAN I KNEW.
GATES: LEWIS PORTER
SURVIVED RESACA,
BUT SOON FACED AN
EVEN GREATER ORDEAL.
JUST DAYS AFTER THE
BATTLE, HE TOOK ILL,
AND WAS SENT TO A
FIELD HOSPITAL.
HE NEVER FULLY RECOVERED.
OVER THE NEXT SIX MONTHS,
LOUIS WAS TREATED IN FOUR
DIFFERENT HOSPITALS, SUFFERING
FROM STOMACH AILMENTS THAT
WOULD PERSIST FOR
DECADES FOLLOWING THE WAR.
ONE OF HIS DOCTOR'S DESCRIBED
HIS CONDITION IN SOME DETAIL,
AS PART OF LEWIS'S APPLICATION
FOR AN INVALID PENSION,
FILED IN 1882.
GABBARD: "I HAVE CAREFULLY
EXAMINED LEWIS PORTER,
LATE A PRIVATE, CO. A.,
105TH REG'T, OHIO INFANTRY
WHO IS AN APPLICANT
FOR AN INVALID PENSION,
THE SAID LEWIS PORTER IS
ONE-FOURTH INCAPACITATED.
THE DISABILITY IS
PROBABLY PERMANENT.
LEWIS PORTER STATES THAT
HE SUFFERS AND THAT HE IS
LABORING UNDER THE
DISEASE AT THIS TIME."
THIS IS 1882.
GATES: HE WAS DISCHARGED
FROM THE ARMY ON
JULY 22ND, 1865, I MEAN
THE POOR GUY IS STILL.
GABBARD: SUFFERING STILL.
I MEAN THIS UNFORTUNATELY
UM, I MEAN THIS REMINDS ME
OF WHAT I HEAR FROM
VIETNAM VETERANS
WHO CALL AND ASK FOR
HELP AND WHO SIMILARLY
DECADES, DECADES
AFTER COMING HOME
ARE STILL SUFFERING.
GATES: YEAH.
GABBARD: YOU CAN TALK
ABOUT THE DOLLARS AND CENTS,
BUT IT'S NOT TAKING INTO
ACCOUNT THE HUMAN COST AND
WHAT OUR COUNTRY PROMISES
TO THOSE WHO GO AND SERVE.
GATES: WE PROMISE THEM
EVERYTHING AND THEN
TREAT THEM AS IF THEY'RE AN
EMBARRASSMENT TO THE COUNTRY.
GABBARD: SADLY.
GATES: LEWIS PORTER SUFFERED
A GREAT DEAL FOR HIS COUNTRY,
BUT HIS STORY HAS A
SURPRISINGLY HAPPY ENDING.
RECORDS SHOW THAT LEWIS
LIVED TO BE 86 YEARS OLD,
NOT ONLY THAT, HE MANAGED
TO HAVE A FULL LIFE
DESPITE HIS ILLNESS,
MARRYING THREE TIMES,
AND FATHERING AT
LEAST 12 CHILDREN.
GATES: HE MIGHT HAVE BEEN
SICK BUT HE WASN'T DEAD.
GABBARD: THAT'S RIGHT.
GATES: WHAT'S IT BEEN LIKE
FOR YOU TO LEARN THIS STORY?
GABBARD: IT'S INCREDIBLE AND
EXCITING TO HEAR AND IN MY OWN
VERY SMALL WAY BE ABLE TO
RELATE IN SOME FASHION TO THE
CHOICES THAT HE MADE
UM, TO VOLUNTEER AND UM,
GOSH, WHAT HE WENT THROUGH.
GATES: DID IT EVER OCCUR TO
YOU WHEN YOU'RE FIGHTING TO
GET YOUR NAME ADDED TO THE
DEPLOYMENT LIST THAT BASICALLY
YOU'RE CHANNELING YOUR
THIRD GREAT-GRANDFATHER.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE
CARRYING OUT A TRADITION.
GABBARD: NOW I KNOW
WHERE I GET IT FROM.
GATES: YEAH. THAT'S
ASTONISHING, ISN'T IT?
GABBARD: THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
YEAH.
GATES: WE HAD ALREADY TRACED
MARCO RUBIO'S FATHER'S FAMILY
FROM THE STREETS OF HAVANA
TO THE COURTYARDS OF SEVILLE.
NOW, TURNING TO
HIS MOTHER'S ROOTS,
WE EXPECTED TO MAKE
A SIMILAR JOURNEY,
BUT OUR SEARCH
LED US ELSEWHERE.
WE STARTED WITH
MARCO'S GRANDFATHER,
PEDRO GARCIA, A MAN WHOSE
LIFE WAS MARKED BY HARDSHIP.
RUBIO: MY GRANDFATHER HAD
AN UP OR DOWN EXISTENCE.
YOU KNOW, HE AT ONE POINT HAD
A PRETTY GOOD JOB WORKING IN
A, FOR THE RAILROAD COMPANY
OR WHATEVER IT WAS AND
THEN HE LOST THAT JOB,
AND THEN HE STRUGGLED.
HE HAD BEEN UH, HANDICAPPED
AS A BOY WITH POLIO.
AND THERE WERE TIMES WHERE HE
REALLY STRUGGLED TO PROVIDE
FOR THEM BECAUSE
PHYSICALLY HE COULDN'T,
YOU KNOW, DO SOME OF THE WORK
THAT OTHER PEOPLE COULD DO.
GATES: PEDRO IMMIGRATED TO
AMERICA FROM CUBA IN THE 1950S.
MARCO KNEW HIM, AND
REMEMBERS HIM FONDLY AS
A MAN WHO LOVED HISTORY
AND LOVED STORY-TELLING.
BUT PEDRO RARELY SPOKE
ABOUT HIS CHILDHOOD,
AND MARCO KNOWS NEXT TO
NOTHING ABOUT HIS ROOTS.
RUBIO: I JUST KNOW HE WAS
ONE OF A LOT OF KIDS AND,
AND YOU KNOW, THE STORY
ALWAYS WAS HIS PARENTS,
I'M NOT SURE
WERE EVEN MARRIED.
GATES: MARCO, THEY
HAD 17 CHILDREN.
RUBIO: ALL FROM HER?
GATES: ALL FROM HER.
RUBIO: THAT'S SOMETHING ELSE.
GATES: THAT'S HARD WORK.
RUBIO: YEAH.
GATES: DO YOU HAVE ANY
IDEA WHERE THIS PART OF
YOUR FAMILY CAME FROM?
RUBIO: I DON'T.
WE ARE NOW AT THE LIMITS OF
MY KNOWLEDGE OF MY FAMILY'S
ANCESTRY, RIGHT HERE.
GATES: TO PUSH BEYOND THE
LIMITS OF MARCO'S KNOWLEDGE
REQUIRED SOME LUCK.
WE WERE ABLE TO LEARN VERY
LITTLE ABOUT PEDRO'S FATHER
CARLOS, AND WE COULD ONLY
TRACE HIS MOTHER RAMONA BACK
ONE GENERATION, TO THE 1850S.
BUT TURNING TO PEDRO'S WIFE,
A WOMAN NAMED DOMINGA
RODRÍGUEZ Y CHIROLDE,
WE WERE ABLE TO GO MUCH
FURTHER BACK IN TIME.
MANY OF HER ANCESTORS
LIVED IN PINAR DEL RÍO,
A LARGELY RURAL
PROVINCE IN WESTERN CUBA,
WHERE WE FOUND A SERIES OF
BAPTISM AND MARRIAGE RECORDS
TAKING HER ROOTS
BACK ALMOST 300 YEARS.
MEANING MARCO RUBIO'S FAMILY
HAS LIVED IN CUBA FOR MUCH
LONGER THAN HE EVER DREAMED.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT THE NAME OF
YOUR FIFTH GREAT-GRANDFATHER.
RUBIO: MANUEL
RICARDO DEL ALDANA?
GATES: HAVE YOU
EVER HEARD OF HIM?
RUBIO: NO.
GATES: HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF THAT SURNAME, ALDANA?
RUBIO: I'VE HEARD IT,
BUT I CAN'T CONNECT IT
TO ANYBODY OR ANYTHING.
GATES: YOUR FIFTH GREAT-
GRANDFATHER WOULD'VE
BEEN BORN AROUND 1730.
RUBIO: 1730.
GATES: SENATOR, THERE ARE
A LOT OF AMERICANS WHOSE
ANCESTRY HAILS FROM
NORTHERN EUROPE WHO
CANNOT GO BACK THIS FAR.
RUBIO: GET THIS FAR? YEAH.
GATES: IN THEIR FAMILY TREE.
RUBIO: YEAH. THAT'S
AMAZING, IT REALLY IS.
NO ONE CAN SAY I'M NOT CUBAN.
GATES: NOBODY.
RUBIO: YEAH.
GATES: MARCO WAS SURPRISED TO
SEE THAT HIS MATERNAL ROOTS
RAN SO DEEPLY IN CUBA,
HE'D EXPECTED THEM TO
TRACE IN THE NEAR
PAST BACK TO SPAIN,
AS WE'D SEEN ON
HIS FATHER'S SIDE.
BUT HE WAS EVEN MORE SURPRISED
BY WHAT RECORDS REVEALED ABOUT
HIS THIRD GREAT-GRANDFATHER, A
MAN NAMED JUAN JOSÉ CHIROLES.
HE WAS A LANDOWNER.
HE OWNED A TOBACCO FARM.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
RUBIO: I DID NOT.
I HAD NO CLUE.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME EVER THAT
SOMEONE SAYS THAT ANYBODY IN
MY LINEAGE OWNED ANYTHING
IN CUBA BEYOND THE
CLOTHES ON THEIR BACK.
GATES: AS IT TURNS OUT, JUAN
OWNED ROUGHLY 30 ACRES OF LAND
ON WHICH HE GREW
TOBACCO, CORN AND RICE,
BUT THAT WASN'T ALL HE OWNED.
WE FOUND THE BAPTISMAL RECORD
FOR A CHILD BORN TO HIS SLAVE.
RUBIO: "I, THE PINAR
DEL RÍO PARISH PRIEST,
SOLEMNLY BAPTIZED ISABEL, BORN
ON THE 19TH OF LAST MONTH,
DAUGHTER OF THE "MOREAN
CRIOLLA" ANGELA AND AN
UNKNOWN FATHER, BOTH SLAVES
OF JUAN JOSÉ CHIROLDE,
WHO LIVES IN THIS PARISH."
WOW.
THAT'S WHAT I FEARED WHEN WE
WERE GOING INTO THIS WHOLE
EXPERIENCE ABOUT THE
LAND AND SO FORTH.
THAT WAS GONNA BE MY
FOLLOW-UP QUESTION,
BUT I DIDN'T WANT TO
KNOW THE ANSWER, SO.
GATES: DID YOU EVER IMAGINE
THAT YOU HAD A SLAVE OWNER
IN YOUR FAMILY TREE?
RUBIO: NO, I DIDN'T.
I MEAN I DIDN'T THINK
THEY OWNED ANY LAND,
SO I DIDN'T THINK
THEY COULD OWN PEOPLE.
GATES: WHAT ARE YOU FEELING?
RUBIO: IT'S JUST HARD TO
KIND OF PROCESS IT ALL.
I MEAN IF YOU BAPTIZED THEM
IT'S BECAUSE YOU BELIEVED THEY
HAD A SOUL AND WERE
CREATED IN GOD'S IMAGE.
HOW THEN COULD
YOU OWN THEM AS A,
AS A PIECE OF
CATTLE OR YOU KNOW AND,
AND, AND AS A, AS, I
JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT.
GATES: DOES THIS CHANGE THE
WAY THAT YOU THINK OF THIS
PART OF YOUR FAMILY'S HISTORY?
RUBIO: YEAH.
I MEAN OBVIOUSLY IT'S JUST
NOT SOMETHING I EVER THOUGHT,
YOU KNOW, I
NEVER THOUGHT OF IT.
I JUST DIDN'T
THINK IT WAS THERE.
YOU SORT OF SEE LIKE ONE
GENERATION OWNS LAND AND
UM, SADLY OWNS HUMAN
BEINGS AND ALL THAT,
AND, AND WITHIN
TWO GENERATIONS,
I MEAN, THEY'RE BARELY
FEEDING THEIR KIDS,
AND THEY'RE STRUGGLING TO
PROVIDE FOR THEIR FAMILIES.
I MEAN IT JUST TELLS YOU
HOW QUICKLY PEOPLE'S
FORTUNES CHANGE, RIGHT?
GATES: REVERSAL OF FORTUNE.
RUBIO: WOW.
GATES: THE PAPER TRAIL HAD NOW
RUN OUT FOR EACH OF MY GUESTS.
IT WAS TIME TO SEE WHAT
DNA COULD REVEAL ABOUT
THEIR DEEPER ROOTS.
WE'D ALREADY SHOWN PAUL RYAN
THAT HIS ADMIXTURE REVEALED
HIDDEN JEWISH ANCESTRY.
FOR TULSI GABBARD, THE SAME
TEST REFLECTED THE ENORMOUS
DIVERSITY WE'D SEEN
IN HER GENEALOGY,
TYING HER TO ETHNIC
GROUPS ACROSS THE GLOBE,
FROM NORTHERN EUROPE,
TO SOUTHEAST ASIA!
GABBARD: GOSH.
THIS JUST SHOWS HOW
CONNECTED WE ALL ARE.
GATES: INDEED.
GABBARD: THIS IS
FURTHER PROOF AND EVIDENCE.
WHEN WE LOOK AT OUR LIVES AND
THOSE WHO'VE COME BEFORE US
WE'RE ALL CONNECTED.
GATES: WE'RE ALL CONNECTED.
TURNING TO MARCO RUBIO, WE HAD
ONE FINAL REVELATION TO SHARE.
WHEN WE ANALYZED HIS
MITOCHONDRIAL DNA,
A GENETIC FINGERPRINT PASSED
DOWN UNCHANGED FROM MOTHER TO
CHILD FOR THOUSANDS OF YEARS,
WE FOUND THAT HIS DIRECT
MATERNAL LINE WAS
NATIVE AMERICAN.
ONE OF YOUR GREAT-GREAT-
GREAT-GRANDMOTHERS
WAS A PURE NATIVE AMERICAN.
RUBIO: YEAH, WOW,
LOOK AT THAT.
GATES: SCHOLARS BELIEVE THAT
THE NATIVE AMERICAN POPULATION
IN PINAR DEL RÍO MIGRATED
FROM THE YUCATÁN PENINSULA
ABOUT 4000 BC.
RUBIO: RIGHT.
GATES: SO, TALK
ABOUT, YOU KNOW,
ANCESTRAL ROOTS IN CUBA, YOUR
FAMILY ON YOUR NATIVE AMERICAN
LINE'S BEEN THERE
FOR A LONG, LONG TIME.
RUBIO: RIGHT. I'VE BEEN TO
THOSE RUINS IN THE YUCATÁN.
GATES: OH YEAH?
RUBIO: AT CHICHEN ITZA,
AND WHO KNEW I WAS
GOING BACK HOME?
GATES: MARCO'S DNA UNDERSCORES
A LARGER POINT: ALMOST EVERY
AMERICAN DESCENDS FROM
SOMEONE WHO WASN'T BORN
IN OUR COUNTRY, BUT HAS
EMBRACED, AND ENRICHED
IT JUST THE SAME.
WE'D SEEN THIS OVER AND OVER
IN MY GUESTS' FAMILY TREES,
AND ITS RELEVANCE WASN'T
LOST ON ANY OF THEM,
LEAST OF ALL ON MARCO RUBIO.
RUBIO: THIS REALLY BRINGS
IT TO LIGHT ABOUT AMERICA.
IN AMERICA WE DON'T
HAVE A COMMON ETHNICITY,
A COMMON LANGUAGE.
I MEAN THERE'S, THERE ARE
COUNTRIES IN THIS WORLD THAT
DOING THE DNA OF THE
POPULATION WOULD NOT BE
VERY COMPLICATED, EVERYONE AT
SOME POINT IS PRETTY SIMILAR.
GATES: LIKE ICELAND.
RUBIO: LIKE, YEAH, RIGHT.
SO, I, AND OTHER PLACES.
AND, BUT IN AMERICA WE'RE,
IT'S NOT JUST A GENETIC MIX.
WE COME FROM DIFFERENT
CONTINENTS AND DIFFERENT
PARTS OF THE WORLD.
IF YOU GO FAR ENOUGH,
WE COME FROM EVERYWHERE.
BUT I'VE ALWAYS SAID THAT THE
ONE THING WE HAVE IN COMMON
IN ALL OF OUR DNA AS
AMERICANS IS WE ALL
DESCEND FROM GO-GETTERS.
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF US
DESCENDS FROM SOMEONE
WHO OVERCAME INCREDIBLE
ADVERSITY, WHETHER IT WAS
UH, THE JOURNEY THAT
BROUGHT THEM INTO,
INTO SLAVERY AND THEN SURVIVED
IT IN BRUTAL CONDITIONS FOR
HUNDREDS OF YEARS, WHETHER
IT'S SOMEONE WHO CAME LAST
WEEK FROM ANOTHER COUNTRY
IN SEARCH OF A BETTER LIFE,
OR SOMEONE WHO CAME
200 YEARS AGO IN
SEARCH OF A BETTER LIFE.
OUR COMMON DNA IN AMERICA IS
WE ALMOST ALL DESCEND FROM A
GO-GETTER, SOMEONE WHO REFUSED
TO ACCEPT THE LIMITS PUT UPON
THEM IN THE OLD WORLD, AND
SO THEY REACHED FOR THIS ONE
PLACE WHERE THEY WERE GONNA
BE JUDGED BY WHO THEY WERE,
NOT WHERE THEY CAME FROM.
GATES: THAT'S THE END
OF OUR JOURNEY WITH
MARCO, TULSI, AND PAUL.
JOIN ME NEXT TIME
WHEN WE UNLOCK THE
SECRETS OF THE PAST
FOR NEW GUESTS ON
ANOTHER EPISODE OF
"FINDING YOUR ROOTS".
TO ORDER THIS PROGRAM ON DVD,
VISIT SHOP PBS OR CALL
1-800-PLAY-PBS.
THIS PROGRAM IS ALSO AVAILABLE
ON AMAZON PRIME VIDEO.
NARRATOR: CORPORATE FUNDING
FOR "FINDING YOUR ROOTS"
WAS PROVIDED BY:
WHEN WE LEARN
ERE WE COME FROM,
WE LEARN A DEEPER
STORY ABOUT OURSELVES.
AT ANCESTRY, THERE
ARE DIFFERENT PATHS
TO DISCOVERING YOUR STORY.
FROM BUILDING
YOUR FAMILY TREE,
TO LEARNING YOUR
FULL ETHNICITY
AND REVEALING ANCESTORS
YOU NEVER KNEW YOU HAD.
ANCESTRY HELPS YOU CONNECT
TO YOUR UNIQUE STORY.
MAN: WE ALL COME FROM SUCH
DIFFERENT BACKGROUNDS
THAT YOU NEVER KNOW.
NARRATOR: LEARN MORE
AT ANCESTRY.COM.
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER WE'VE
ALWAYS BEEN CONNECTED.
AT AT&T WE'RE CONTINUING TO
CREATE TECHNOLOGY THAT WILL
HELP PEOPLE STAY CONNECTED
NOW AND INTO THE FUTURE.
IN THE 1950S JAUNDICE WAS A
LEADING CAUSE OF INFANT DEATH.
UNTIL A NURSE FOUND
THAT SUNLIGHT COULD CURE
THE CONDITION.
MAJOR FUNDING WAS PROVIDED BY:
THE FORD FOUNDATION,
WORKING WITH VISIONARIES ON THE
FRONT LINES OF
SOCIAL CHANGE WORLDWIDE.
BY CANDACE KING WEIR,
THE LLOYD CARNEY FOUNDATION,
THE ROBERT WOOD
JOHNSON FOUNDATION,
BY THE CORPORATION
FOR PUBLIC BROADCASTING
AND BY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO THIS PBS STATION
FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU,
THANK YOU.
♪ ♪
BE MORE PBS
New Aveeno® MaxGlow™
Infusion Drops
with kiwi to lock moisture.
And soy to even skin tone.
Unleash dewy, glowing skin from
within.
New Aveeno® MaxGlow™.
>> LIKE IT OR NOT THE ESQUIRE
COVER THAT SOME PEOPLE ARE
CALLING INSENSITIVE AND
IGNORANT.
WE WILL GET INTO THAT.
PLUS:
>> GEORGE CLOONEY DEFENDS A
MEMBER OF THE ROYAL FAMILY,
AND MAKES SOME EYE-OPENING
PRINCESS DI COMPARISONS.
AND SHOULD YOU GET A SUPERBOWL
RING?
IF YOU WEREN'T IN THE SUPER
BOWL?
THAT AND MORE TONIGHT ON FOX5
LIKE IT OR NOT.
>> ♪ ♪.
>> HEY, GUESS WHAT?
WE MIGHT NOT BE TALKING ABOUT
A WALL SOON.
>> REALLY?
>> THERE IS A COMPROMISE THAT
APPARENTLY IS HAPPENING,
RIGHT?
>> SOME BREAKING NEWS?
>> LAST NIGHT?
GEEZ.
>> LET'S FACE IT.
>> OH, MY BAD.
>> OH, IT HAPPENED 38 MINUTE
AGO.
MY BAD.
IT GIVES US MORE TIME TO TALK
ABOUT WHITE GUYS.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
IT IS SO TOUGH BEING A WHITE
GUY THESE DAYS.
JUST ASK ESQUIRE MAGAZINE.
WE'LL FIRE IT UP WITH THAT.
OH, THE TRIALS AND
TRIBULATIONS CENTS OF THE
WHITE MALE.
CHRONICLED BY THE COVER STORY
LATEST ISSUE OF ESQUIRE.
THAT IS POOR 17 YEAR OLD RYAN
MORGAN FROM WISCONSIN, THE
QUINESSENTIAL QUOTE AMERICAN
BOY.
WHAT IT IS LIKE TO GROW UP
WHITE, MIDDLE CLASS, AND MALE
IN THE ERA OF SOCIAL MEDIA
SCHOOL SHOOTINGS, TOXIC MASSES
CUE LYNN AT THIS, ME TOO AND
DIVIDED COUNTRY.
>> THIS PIECE IS ABOUT THE
ADVERSE AT THIS OF BEING A
TRUMP SUPPORTER.
ESQUIRE EDITOR IN CHIEF SAID
MORGAN'S COVER STORY IS
ACTUALLY AN INSTALLMENT IN A
SERIES ON GROWING UP IN THE
PRESENT POLITICAL AT MOSS
CENTS FEAR.
IT WILL FEATURE BLACK LGBTQ
AND FEMALE STORIES AS WELL,
BUT THEY STARTED WITH THE
WHITE GUY.
TWITTER HAD IT WAY WITH THE
MAG A SEEN.
ONE QUOTE ESQUIRE CEO.
QUOTE WE SHOULD PROBABLY DO A
COVER STORY FOR BLACK HISTORY
MONTH.
ANY SUGGESTIONS CENTS?
EDITOR, THERE IS A WHITE BOY
IN WISCONSIN WHO IS SAD.
ESQUIRE CEO, QUOTE, RUN IT.
IS THIS REALLY MAN AT HIS
BEST, NICK?
LIKE IT OR NOT.
>> I AM GOING TO GIVE THEM A
PASON THIS AND I SAY THIS
SIMPLY BECAUSE I DO THINK IT
IS TOUGH AC TEENAGER IN 2019.
THE ISSUE IS ACTUALLY THE
MARCH ISSUE.
AND I THINK THAT MORE
IMPORTANTLY, WE HAVE GOT TO
LEARN TO START LISTENING TO
EACH OTHER, START HAVING
CONVERSATIONS SO WE'RE NOT
SHOCK BY SITUATIONS CENTS LIKE
NORTHAM, NOT SHOCK BY
TEENAGERS WHO TALK OTHERS INTO
SUICIDE, THE ONE WHO JUST GOT
CONVICTED A LOT HAPPENING WITH
YOUNG PEOPLE TODAY.
SOCIAL MEDIA DOES NOT HELP.
WE HAVE THE ABILITY TO
NAVIGATE IT.
I THINK BETTER THAN MOST,
BECAUSE WE'RE NOT IN THE EYE
OF THAT STORM.
WE CAN LEAVE IT.
WE CAN CHOOSES TO ENGAGE.
SO I'M GOING TO GIVE THEM A
PASS.
THEY SAY THIS IS AN
INSTALLMENT.
MARINA I'M HOPING THAT THEY'LL
HIGHLIGHT YOUNG WOMEN ALSO
STRUGGLING AND PEOPLE OF
COLOR.
>> WE'RE NOT WOMEN -- WE'RE
NOT THE TARGET AUDIENCE FOREST
CHOIR, I THINK MEN ARE, AND I
DON'T SEE WHAT THE PROBLEM S I
DON'T SEE WHY WE'VE GOT TO
SILENCE ANYBODY.
I MEAN IF THIS KID HAS CENTS A
STORY TELL THE STORY CLEARLY
THEY THOUGHT THAT THIS WOULD
CAUSE AN UPROAR, AS IT DID,
AND THEY DID IT ON BLACK
HISTORY MONTH.
WHICH I THINK THEY DID ON
PURPOSE.
BECAUSE THEY WANTED PEOPLE TO
SAY WHY AREN'T WE PROMOTING
AND WHY AREN'T WE HIGHLIGHTING
OTHER STORIES, BUT WE'RE
TELLING THIS CHILD'S STORYRY
WHICH I THINK HE HAS A STORY
TO TELL.
I DON'T SEE WHY.
>> WHICH IS WHAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW, STORY TO TELL
LIKE EVERYBODY DOES, WHAT,
YOU'RE WHITE AND YOU'RE A MAN
AND WE CAN'T TALK ABOUT YOU?
>> OUT OF PLACE, JUST TONE
DEAF.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S THE POINT OF TELLING
THIS STOREY?
OH, I'M SORRY YOU'RE A HIGH
SCHOOLER WITH TROUBLE BECAUSE
YOU WEAR A MAGA HAT TO HIGH
SCHOOL?
I NEED TO HEAR THAT SOB
STOREY?
>> HE REALLY DOES HAVE A STORY
TO TELL.
>> RIGHT.
>> WELL, IT IS NOT NECESSARILY
A SOB STORY, BUT IT IS HIS
STORY AND IT IS UNIQUE, THAT
WHAT MAKES AMERICA.
WE ARE ALL UNIQUE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> WE'RE A MELTING POT.
NOW TIMING IS THE ISSUE.
JUST CAME OUT AT THE WRONG
TIME.
YOU KNOW, WHO EVER ADVERTISED
IT GO AHEAD AND MAKE THIS,
PRODUCE THIS FOR THE MONTH OF
FEBRUARY EVEN THOUGH IT COMES
OUT IN MARCH IT, HIT THE
STANDS.
>> CENTS IT IS OUT NOW.
>> YES.
>> WHICH IS BLACK HISTORY
MONTH.
WOULD YOU THINK WHEN WE'RE
RECOGNIZING DEMOGRAPHIC THEY
WOULD STICK TO THAT
DEMOGRAPHIC.
>> DISCUSSION AT WOODROW
WILSON HIGH SCHOOL WHETHER TO
CHANGE THE NAME OF THE SCHOOL.
NOW HAS INVITED STUDENT,
PARENT, TEACH TEARS JOIN THE
CONVERSATION.
THE GROUP SAYS PRESIDENT
WOODROW WILL SO SEGREGATION
VIEWS AND VOCAL DEFENSE OF THE
KKK RAISES QUESTIONS ABOUT
WHETHER HE SHOULD HAVE HAD A
HIGH SCHOOL NAMED AFTER HIM.
NOW THE SCHOOL FIRST OPENED
ITS DOORS BACK IN 1935.
NAME CHANGE GUY LIKE IT OR
NOT.
>> I LIKE THIS A LOT.
BEAUTY ABOUT ALL OF THIS THAT
WE'RE HAVING DISCUSSION ABOUT
CHANGE.
AND WE ALL KNOW CHANGE AIN'T
EASY TO ACTUALLY IMPLEMENT.
WITH THIS, YOU LOOK AT IT, YOU
GOT TO SAY WELL HEY THEY'VE
IDENTIFY ADD PROBLEM, NOW
ADDRESSING THE PROBLEM AND I
EXPECT MORE SCHOOLS PROBABLY
TO FOLLOW SUIT.
I WOULD ALSO SAY THAT I DON'T
THINK WE SHOULD COMPLETELY
ERASE THE HISTORY OF WOODROW
WILSON, PART OF THE HISTORY,
IF ANYTHING, THEY SHOULD
RENAME THE SCHOOL AND MAKE
SURE THAT KIDS THAT NOW
ATTENDS THAT SCHOOL KNOW THE
HISTORY, KNOW IT ONCE WAS
CENTS NAMED WOODROW WILSON,
LOU WHAT WE ARE AND BECOME.
>> INTERESTING, BECAUSE
SOMEBODY IN THE STORY WAS
SAYING THEY HAD NO IDEA OTHER
THAN WOODROW WILSON WAS
PRESIDENT, WHAT HE STOOD FOR,
WHAT HAPPENED, AND HE CLEARLY
HAD A LOT OF FOREIGN POLICY,
BUT OBVIOUSLY DIDN'T KNOW HIS
HISTORY RIGHT?
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,  THIS IS
COMMUNITY POLITICS.
SO THIS COMMUNITY WANT TO
CHANGE IT.
AND THEY GO ABOUT THE PROPER
PROCESS.
AND IT IS APPROVED.
WHY NOT?
>> IF THIS COMMUNITY WANTS TO&
CHANGE IT AND THEY GO ABOUT
THE PROCESS THEN I SEE NO
PROBLEM WITH T BUT IF WE ARE
TALKING ABOUT JUST SWEEPING
CHANGES, TO ERASE THAT
HISTORY, I'M NOT SURE THAT
THAT'S THE SMART THING TO DO
PARTICULARLY SINCE WILSON WAS
A PRESIDENT.
IF WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
MONUMENT, I'M TOTALLY FOR IT,
MONUMENTS I THINK TAKE ON
DIFFERENT SIGNIFICANCE, BUT I
DON'T THINK WE SHOULD ERASE
THE HISTORY OF WILSON IF IT IS
ABOUT CHANGING IT BECAUSE HE
HAD VIEWS THAT ARE COUNTER TO
MY OWN.
WE ARE NOW IN A SYSTEM AND
SITUATION WHERE WE HEARD
PEOPLE STIRRING UP CONTROVERSY
AROUND PRESIDENT CLINTON.
I DON'T DOUBT THAT IN 20 YEARS
THE IDEA OF SEXUAL ASSAULT
WON'T BE SOMETHING THAT'S
PASSE, THAT WE WILL TAKE A
HARDER STANCE.
I DON'T WANT US RELEASING THE
LEGACY.
>> YOU CAN DO THIS WITH MOST
PRESIDENTS, PROBABLY FINDS
SOMETHING WRONG WITH THEIR
POLICIES.
WAS NAMED IN 1935, VERY
DIFFERENT TIME.
BUT I'M WITH THE COMMUNITY
HERE.
THIS IS THEIR DECISION,  THIS
IS THEIR SCHOOL.
THEY CAN MAKE A CHOICE WHETHER
THEY'RE OFFENDED BY THAT NAME
TO BE ON THE SCHOOL AND CHANGE
THE NAME.
JUST BECAUSE IT WAS UP THERE
ONCE DOESN'T MEAN IT IS CENTS
THERE --
>> INDEED.
COMING UP HERE SOME SAY THE
TAXI INDUSTRY IN THE DISTRICT
IS DOOMED.
THE PATRIOTS WHO DIDN'T PLAY
IN THE SUPER BOWL, BUT STILL
GETTING A RING.
PLUS GEORGE CLOONEY MAKES
SURPRISING COMPARISON, BETWEEN
MEGHAN MARKLE AND PRINCESS DI.
FOX5 LIKE IT OR NOT WILL BE
RIGHT BACK.
>> QUESTION:  IS THE TAXI CAB
INDUSTRY IN THE DISTRICT
DOOMED?
ACCORDING TO WTLP TRIPLE A
SAYS THERE HAS BEEN 32% DROP
IN THE NUMBER OF TIMES A TAXI
WAS HAILED IN D.C. IN THE
LASTS THREE YEARS.
EVEN THOUGH FARES CHARGED BY
CAB DRIVERS ARE GENERALLY
CHEAPER ON QUICK TRIPS THAN
APP BASED FARES, ALSO REPORT
BY THE DC COUNCIL, SAYS RIDE
HAILING SERVICES CENTS LIKE
UBER AND LYFT LEAD TO TRAFFIC
CONGESTION AND ADD WEAR AND
TEAR TO THE DISTRICT'S ROADS.
BUT IS THERE A WAY TO STOP
THIS FROM HAPPENING?
THE DOOMED TAXI CAB INDUSTRY.
MARINA, LIKE IT OR NOT?
>> IT IS 2019.
I DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
I GET WHY THEY'RE UPSET.
BUT BY THIS POINT THEY SHOULD
HAVE FIGURED THIS OUT F LYFT
AND UBER THRIVING, AND THEY'VE
DONE IT ONLY BASED ON AN APP,
WHAT'S DIFFERENT BETWEEN AN
UBER CAR AND TAXI CAB?
NOTHING RIGHT?
SO YOU IMPLEMENT THAT SAME
SORT OF COMPETITIVENESS,
RIGHT, YOU PUT THE APP IN
PLACE YOU HAVE COMPETITIVE
PRICES CENTS AND BOOM, YOU'RE
BACK IN THE BUSINESS.
WHY CAN'T THEY DO THIS?
WHY DO THEY WANT TO STICK TO
THE OLD WAYS?
THINGS WILL EVOLVE.
THINGS WILL CHANGE, IT IS
2019, SOMETHING WILL COME UP
IN TO 20, THEY'LL BE OUT OF
THE LOOP AGAIN, DO YOU HAVE
STAY UP WITH IT.
>> YOU HIT HOMERUN ON THIS
ONE.
THIS IS JUST DOWN RIGHT CRAZY.
LIKE YOU SAY, IT IS 2019.
TALKING ABOUT CAB DRIVERS
COMPLAINING ABOUT NOT GETTING
THE SAME AMOUNT OF MONDAY THAT
I UBER DRIVERS ARE NOW
GETTING?
WAKE UP AND SMELL THE DEAD
ROSES CENTS BECAUSE THIS IS A
DEAD INDUSTRY.
IT IS LIKE YOU GET IN A CAB,
THEY POP IN A CASTLE, ALL
LISTENING TO MP 3'S, THEY NEED
TO I AM PRESENT MEANT
SOMETHING NEW.
BRING IN NEW WAY POSSIBLY NEW
APP SO THEY COMPETE WITH
ACTUAL UBER.
THE ACTUAL CAB DRIVERS.
MAKES $27,000 A YEAR.
I WOULD ADD AN UBER DRIVER
MAKES MORE THAN THAT.
>> THEY'RE TOO LATE.
THEY'VE BEEN SURPASSED.
THERE HAD TO BE MORE THAN ONE
SOFTWARE ENGINEER THAT FIGURED
OUT HOW TO DO THIS.
WHY THESE INDUSTRY
SPECIFICALLY IN NEW YORK AND
IN A PLACE LIKE THERE WHERE
THERE ARE A LOT OF TAXI CAB
DRIVERS, WHY THEY DIDN'T ADAPT
TO THE TECHNOLOGY MAKES
ABSOLUTELY NO SENSE.
WITH THE WEATHER, JUST LIKE
THE LASTS COUPLE EVERY DAYS,
YOU THINK I'M STANDING OUTSIDE
TO HAIL A CAB WHEN I CAN PUSH
A BUTTON ON MY PHONE, THEN
WHEN THE PERSON SHOWS UP I
WALK OUTSIDE?
HELLO.
WAKE UP TO THE FUTURE PEOPLE.
OKAY?
I'M NOT GOING TO USE YOUR
SERVICE, I DON'T CARE IF IT
COST ME DOLLAR MORE, DON'T
GIVE ME THE CONGESTION STUFF
EITHER.
THE MARKET WILL DICTATE HOW
MANY PEOPLE WANT TO USE CARS.
WHETHER THEY'RE TAXICABS OR
UBER OR LIVES.
IT IS ALL THE SAME TO ME.
>> COMPLETELY AGREE, YOU ALL
HAVE SAID IT ALL.
THEY MISSED THE OPPORTUNITY,
AND I FOR ONE WILL GO OUT OF
MY WAY NOT TO TAKE A TAXI.
SO --
>> I HATE EVERYTHING ABOUT THE
TAXI, HATE, TAKE EXTRA TURN,
SHOULD I GO UP SUCH AND SUCH?
I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT THE
ROUTE, TOO, I'M DRUNK.
>> THEY HAVE RUNNING METERS,
RIGHT?
THEY USED TO HAVE THE ZONE
SITUATION HERE, THAT NEVER
MADE ANY SENSE, NEVER,
COMPLETELY, MADE NO SENSE,
CROSS OVER SOME LINE, NOW --
>> YOU HAVE TO PAY EXTRA.
>> COMING UP JOSH GORDON ONE
OF THE PLAYERS INVOLVED IN THE
PERFORMANCE ENHANCING DRUG
SCANDAL.
BUT APPARENTLY HE STILL IS
GETTING A RING BABY WHY?
BECAUSE'S' A PATRIOTS.
SHOULD HE?
Switch to Fios and get
entertainment delivered
to your home like no one else.
Because Fios is a 100%
fiber-optic network.
That means you'll get the
fastest internet available
and Fios TV One with amazing
4K capability,
and an advanced voice remote.
And now we'll give you a Netflix
premium plan for a full year.
So you can stream your favorite
Netflix shows
and movies in 4K on 4
devices at once.
Already have Netflix?
We'll cover the cost for one
year.
Just switch for 79.99 a month
with a two-year agreement
and get Fios Gigabit Connection
with TV and phone
with a 2-year price guarantee.
And not only will you get a
Netflix premium plan on us for a
year,
you'll be able to find Netflix
in the Fios Channel guide
and use the advanced voice
remote to launch Netflix
and easily find all the
channels,movies and shows
you love.
When you think about it,
there are so many entertaining
reasons to switch to Fios.
100% fiber-optic network.
100% phenomenal.
Go to getfios.com today.
>> WHAT TO DO ABOUT MASS
UNEMPLOYMENT, THIS WILL BE A
MASS SOCIAL CHALLENGE.
AND I THINK ULTIMATELY, WE
WILL HAVE TO HAVE SOME KIND OF
UNIVERSAL BASIC INCOME.
I DON'T THINK WE CAN HAVE A
CAN CHOICE.
>> WELCOME BACK, THAT WAS '
LONG MUSK BACK IN 2017 TALKING
ABOUT UNIVERSAL BASIC INCOME.
IT IS CENTS AN EXPERIMENT, ON
THE MATTER, AND IT WAS JUST
DONE IN FINLAND.
IT WAS CENTS CARRIED OUT BY
THE GOVERNMENT, AND GAVE
UNEMPLOYED PEOPLE, NO STRINGS
ATTACHED GUARANTEE INCOME,
INSTEAD EVERY UNEMPLOYMENT THE
RESULTS, WELL, PEOPLE SAY THEY
WERE HAPPIER AND LESS
STRESSED, BUT IT DID NOT MAKE
THEM ANY MORE LIKELY TO GET A
NEW GIG, MEANWHILE DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE ANKLE
DREW YANK BEHIND UNIVERSAL
BASIC INCOME BUT IS IT
SOMETHING THAT WORKS?
UNIVERSAL BASIC INCOME, GRAM,
LIKE IT OR NOT?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHETHER IT
WORKS OR NOT.
I WILL SAY THIS.
I FIRMLY AGREE WITH ANDREW
YANK, AND ' LONG MUSK, AND
OTHER, THROUGH THE YEARS, AND
IN OTHER COUNTRIES THAT
BELIEVE THAT THIS IS
NECESSARY, FOR THIS MAIN ONE
REASON.
THERE ARE A LOT OF JOBS THAT
ARE GOING TO GO AWAY HERE,
BECAUSE OF AUTOMATION.
IT IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
THERE ARE GOING TO BE DRIVER
LESS CARS, THERE WILL BE
INDUSTRIES, AI IS TAKING OVER
THE COMPANIES WILL FINDS WAYS
TO DO THESE JOBS WITHOUT
PEOPLE.
AND THIS IS WHERE WE
ECONOMICALLY ARE GOING TO HAVE
A MASSIVE PROBLEM.
IS THIS THE ANSWER?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE THE STEP
TOWARD A SOLUTION.
OTHERWISE, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
A LOT OF PEOPLE ON WELFARE,
AND THIS SEEMS LIKE A MORE
FAIR BALD WAY TO ADDRESS THOSE
NEEDS.
>> WHO IS GOING TO PAY FOR
THAT?
>> YOU TAKE AWAY THE WELFARE
PROGRAMS, PUT TAX ON THE
CONDITIONS, BY ADDING 10%
ACTION TAGS ON WHAT THEY
PRODUCE AND THE MONEY COMES
BACK TO THE PEOPLE.
>> MONEY DOESN'T ADD UP.
YOU WON'T GET TRILLIONS AND
TRILLIONS OF DOLLARS TO PAY
FOR THIS INCOME.
>> YOU ARE IF YOU MAKE THE
COMPANIES WHO DON'T HIRE
PEOPLE PAY THEIR FAIR SHARE,.
>> SOFTWARE AND OTHER
INDUSTRIES, ADAPT TO THE TIMES
AGAIN, IF IT MEANS LEARNING
BINARY CODE AND STARTING TO
LEARN HOW TO CODE THEN THAT'S
WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT'S JUST
WHERE WE LIVE.
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF
MANUFACTURING JOBS.
>> THIS NEW GREEN DEAL EVEN IF
YOU'RE UNWILLING TO WORK, WE,
THE TAXPAYER, ARE GOING TO
FUND TO YOU SIT ON THE COUCH
TO NOT DO NOTHING.
>> THAT WAS A FAUX PAS.
>> IT IS NOT.
>> A REALITY.
>> NO, AND PEOPLE SAID IT,
THEY'RE HAPPIER BUT NOT
WILLING TO LOOK FOR JOBS.
SO CLEARLY THIS ISN'T WORKING
IT YOU'RE NOT INSPIRING PEOPLE
TO GET OUT THERE AND FIND --
>> PEOPLE CAN'T LIVE ON
$12,000 A YEAR, THAT'S THE
REALITY OF IT.
>> IF THERE ARE PEOPLE OUT
THERE ON THE STREET LIVING ON
NO DOLLARS, I'M SURE THAT
PEOPLE CAN LIVE ON 1200 BUCKS.
>> WHAT'S THE SOLUTION WHEN
MILLIONS OF JOBS DISAPPEAR DUE -
>> YOU HAVE HALF OF EUROPE
LIVING UNDER A THOUSAND EUROS
A MONTH ON FAMILIES OF SIX, P
PEOPLE.
>> NOT REALITY THE COST OF
LIVING.
>> HEALTHCARE, THOUGH, MARINE,
A YOU KNOW, THE DEAL IS WE
HAVE TO FIGURE OUT SOMETHING.
THE ANSWER CAN'T BE, IT IS TOO
TOUGH TO DO SO WE DO NOTHING.
WE'VE GOT --
>> NO, THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO
OBVIOUSLY NEED ASSISTANCE, AND
THEY SHOULD BE ASSISTED AND
THAT'S CALDWELL FAIR AND WE'RE
THE TAXPAYERS AND WE SUPPORT
THAT SYSTEM, NOW SITE HERE AND
SAY I'M UNWILLING TO WORK NOW
I HAVE TO PAY SIX OOH DOLLARS
FOR EVERY SINGLE PERSON WHO
SAYS THEY'RE UNWILLING TO
WORK.
>> YOU'RE GETTING THE MONDAY
TIE.
>> PEOPLE ARE ABLE AND
UNWILLING.
>> I WILL WORK, I DON'T NEED
ANYBODY TO PAY FOR ME, I'LL
WORK, THAT'S HOW THE SYSTEM
TOO, CLEARLY DO YOU TOO OR YOU
WON'T BE HERE.
>> I WAS UNEMPLOYED.
I CAN TELL YOU IT IS A
MOTIVATIONAL TOOL.
IT FORCES CENTS TO YOU GET A
NEW JOB.
AT SOME POINT YOU WILL LOSE
THE MONEY IF YOU STAY HOME AND
SIT ON YOUR REAREND, YOU COULD
BE LAZY I DON'T LIKE IT.
>> LET'S MOVE ONTO PEOPLE WHO
DON'T NEED ANY MONETARY HELP,
THE NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS.
JOSH GORDON SUSPENDED BY THE
NFL BACK IN DECEMBER DUE TO
ANOTHER FAILED DRUG TEST,
ACCORDING TO MIKE REESE THE
PATRIOTS ARE GOING TO BE
GIVING HIM A SUPER BOWL RING
ANYWAY.
QUOTE FOR HIS CONTRIBUTIONS TO
THE TEAM'S SUCCESS OVER 11
GAMES AFTER HE WAS BROUGHT IN
FROM CLEVELAND.
EVEN THOUGH HE DIDN'T ACTUALLY
PLAY IN ANY OF THE PLAYOFF
GAMES INCLUDING THE SUPER
BOWL.
YOU MAY REMEMBER PATHS
RECEIVER WAS CENTS SUSPENDED
FOR THE FIRST GAMES OF THE TO
SOME SEASON AFTER VIOLATED THE
NFL POLICY AGAINST PERFORMANCE
ENHANCING DRUGS, HE WAS SUPER
BOWL MVP.
PUT A RING ON IT.
>> LIKE IT OR NOT.
>> EVERYTHING ABOUT IT, IF YOU
GET A TEAM YOU GET A RING.
I DON'T CARE HOW SMALL, HOW
LARGE THE CONTRIBUTION, IT IS
A TEAM SPORT.
I THINK THAT THIS USUAL OOH IS
MUTE.
I REALLY DON'T.
I DON'T SEE WHY IT WOULD BE
RISE TO EVEN THE SLIGHTEST
CONTROVERSY.
>> I THINK IT IS BIGGER THAN.
THAT WILL I THINK WE LIVE IN
THE DAY AND AGE WHERE THE NFL
OVERLOOKS DOMESTIC ABUSE,
LOOKS THE OTHER WAY THERE IS
ORGANIZATION THE PATRIOTS,
WHENEVER YOU STANDS UP
ORGANIZATION AND PATRIOTS IN
THE SAME SENTENCE?
WE SAY PATRIOTS AND CHEATERS.
THEY STAND BY THIS GUY WHO HAS
SUBSTANCE ABUSE ISSUE, MOST
ORGANIZATIONS CENTS WOULDN'T
DO THAT.
FURTHERMORE THEY DECIDED TO
GIFT HIM WITH THE RING.
I THINK THEY DE IS HER AFTER
HIGH FIVE FOR.
THAT ONCE AGAIN LOOK AT THE
CLIMATEMENT LOOK AT HOW THE
NFL TREAT EVERYTHING ELSE.
THEY DESERVE TO BE RECOGNIZED
FOR THIS.
>> ARE WE A WART G CHEATERS
NOW RINGS?
THAT'S HOW I SEE IT, YOU'RE
NOT SUPPOSED TO TAKE THIS
WHILE PERFORMING THIS JOB,
RIGHT, WHATEVER IT MAY BE.
YOU SEE, I WAS GIVING THIS
EXAMPLE EARLIER.
YOU DON'T EVEN SIGN YOUR CARD
IN GOLF AND YOU'RE OUT.
SO IF YOU HAVE BEEN TESTED AND
YOU TEST POSITIVE FOR PD IN
GOLF AND TENTS IS AND TALKING
SING ELSE ACTIVITIES SPORT
YOU'RE OUT.
THIS IS CHECK I HAVE SUPPORT.
OBVIOUSLY DIFFERENT.
BUT I THINK IT IS CENTS
CHEATING.
>> THIS IS COLLECTIVELY
BARGAINED THOUGH.
AND THE UNION TALKS TO THE
NFL.
THE UNION SAYS THIS IS THE
PUNISHMENT FOR DOING SOMETHING
LIKE THIS, HE SERVED HIS
PUNISHMENT.
HE SAT OUT FOUR GAMES, YOU CAN
FEEL, HE PLAYED IN THE GAMES,
HE WON, IN THE CASE OF JOSH
GORDON I FEEL LIKE.
>> THIS EVERY YEAR A SUPER
BOWL TEAM BOWL PLACE, GUYS NOT
THEREFORE THAT REASON WHY IT
BE INJURY, SUSPENSION, TRADE,
IT DOESN'T MEAN THEY WERE PART
THAT FAR, GIVE JOSH GORDON
PART OF HIS RING.
I KNOW HE DIDN'T PLAY IN THE
PLAYOFFS BUT GIVE HIM HIS
RING.
>> HE'LL HAVE AN ASTERISK NEXT
TO HIS NAME BUT IT WON'T BE AS
BIG AS IS THAT RING.
>> THE COMING UP HERE, MEGHAN
MARKLE HAS GOT A HOLLYWOOD BIG
WIG IN HER CORNER THESE DAYS.
GEORGE CLOONEY.
WE WILL TELL YOU WHAT HE IS
SAYING ABOUT HER RIGHT AFTER
THE BREAK.
STAY WITH US.
♪ We buy any car dot com ♪
♪ we buy any car dot com ♪
♪ ANY ANY ANY ANY ♪
Did you know trading in your car
at a dealer could cost
you money?
A recent study found consumers
who trade in their car
pay an average of $990
dollars more.
So don't trade in...
sell it....
to We Buy Any Car.
Learn more and get your free
online valuation
now at we buy any car dot com
♪ Find out how much your car is
worth at WeBuyAnyCar.com ♪
>> BASIC STATISTICS TELL US
THAT.
>> IF IN YOUR FINAL MOMENTS,
YOU SEE DEATH.
>> HELLO.
>> THINK NOT OF DEATH.
THINK OF THE LIVING.
>> AND KNOW THIS IT IS YOUR
SACRIFICE, WILL NOT HAVE BEEN
IN VEIN.
>> BACK ON FOX5 LIKE IT OR NOT
WITH GEORGE CLOONEY'S UPCOMING
HULU SERIES CATCH IT TWO,
WHILE PROMOTING IT SPOKE TO
HOO MAGAZINE TALKED ABOUT HIS
FRIENDS MEGHAN MARKLE YES THE
TWO OF THEM ARE FRIENDS, OSCAR
WINNER DEFENDE MEGAN HOW SHE
IS BEING TREATED BY SOME OF
THE PRESS AND THE PAPARAZZI,
QUOTE, SHE IS A WOMAN WHO IS P
MONTHS PREGNANT AND HAS BEEN
PURSUED AND VILIFIED AND
CHASED IN THE SAME WAY THAT
DIANA WAS, AND IT IS HISTORY
REPEATING IT SELF.
WE'VE SEEN HOW THAT ENDS.
GEORGE WAS OF COURSE REFERRING
TO PRINCESS DIANA'S FATAL
CRASH IN 199 P, IN PARIS, SO
WHAT DO WE THINK OF HIM
COMPARING THE TWO GUY LIKE IT
OR NOT?
>> I LIKE THIS A LOT.
NOTHING LIKE HAVING BIG
BROTHER STANDS UP FOR YOU,
CLOONEY LIKE HER BIG BROTHER
WITH REGARD TO MEGAN, YOU
WON'T SEE ME SHED ANY TEARS.
LOOK, SHE KNOWS WHAT SHE
SIGNED UP FOR.
WHEN YOU BECOME A RULE THE
SCRUTINY YOU FACE IS NO
SECRET.
SHE NEW SHE WOULD FACE THAT,
WHY SHOULD WE FEEL SORRY FOR
HER?
I WOULD ARGUE SHE PROBABLY HAS
MORE POSITIVE THINGS GOING ON
AS IS A ROYAL THAN A LOT MORE
NEGATIVE THINGS, DEAL WITH IT,
YOU'RE A ROYAL.
CAN'T THAN BAD.
>> YES, SHE CAME FROM
HOLLYWOOD.
>> YES, YOU AND MARINA ARE
VICIOUS.
>> LITTLE MORBID, THOUGH.
>> HOW?
>> SAYING IT MIGHT ENDS THE
SAME WAY.
PRINCESS DIANA DIED IN A
CRASH.
>> BECAUSE THE PAPARAZZI WERE
CHASING HER THROUGH TUNNELS,
AND I MEAN, THAT'S REALLY
MORBID THING TO SAY.
>> PRINCE HARRY AND EVERYBODY
ELSE.
>> BUT TO SAY IT MIGHT END, WE
SAW HOW THAT ONE ENDED IS
FOREBODING AND VERY MORBID AND
SCARY.
I DIDN'T LIKE THAT.
LIKE THE IDEA THAT SHE IS
GOING TO DIE YOUNG, I DIDN'T
LIKE THE IDEA OF THAT.
>> I DO THINK SHE DESERVES A
LITTLE SYMPATHY.
I DON'T KNOW YOU KNOW WHAT IT
IS LIKE TO BE A ROYAL UNTIL
YOU'RE A ROYAL.
LIKE THE PRESIDENCY I DON'T
KNOW YOU KNOW WHAT THE
PRESIDENT IS UNTIL YOU'VE A
PRESIDENT.
>> THEN DON'T RUN FOR IT.
>> OH, DON'T FALL IN LOVE.
>> OH, SURE IT IS LOVE.
>> OH.
>> THE CONTROL ROOM, WITH
ANOTHER BIG HOLLYWOOD TALKER.
>> I LOVE MARINE, A I LOVE
DOING ROYAL STORIES WHEN
MARINA IS ON, SO MUCH.
BUT YOU GUYS DID YOU WATCH THE
CROWN?
>> YES.
>> NO.
>> OH, MY, FIRST OF ALL,
PLEASE WATCH THE CROWN.
IT IS GREAT.
>> NO.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU CAN'T WATCH THE CROWN?
>> NO.
>> I LIKE MRS. CENTS MAZEL.
>> YOU CAN'T WATCH THE CROWN?
>> WHAT I LIKE ABOUT THE CROWN
>> I LIKE MRS. CENTS MAZEL.
IT, GIVES YOU SORT OF AN
>> WHAT I LIKE ABOUT THE CROWN
INSIGHT INTO THE OTHER SIDE.
IT, GIVES YOU SORT OF AN
YOU KNOW, AGAIN, I AGREE WITH
INSIGHT INTO THE OTHER SIDE.
A GUY BOO HOO ROYALS, BUT SORT
YOU KNOW, AGAIN, I AGREE WITH
OF GIVES YOU INSIGHT INTO WHAT
A GUY BOO HOO ROYALS, BUT SORT
THEY GO THROUGH.
OF GIVES YOU INSIGHT INTO WHAT
BUT SWITCHING GEARS
THEY GO THROUGH.
COMPLETELY, I SAW THE STORY
BUT SWITCHING GEARS
TODAY.
COMPLETELY, I SAW THE STORY
I HAD TO DO IT.
TODAY.
>> SO YOU GUYS KNOW I WAS
I HAD TO DO IT.
CENTS AT E FOR LONG TIME,
>> SO YOU GUYS KNOW I WAS
PEOPLE ALWAYS ASK ME OH, WHO,
CENTS AT E FOR LONG TIME,
WHO IS THE BEST CELEBRITY YOU
PEOPLE ALWAYS ASK ME OH, WHO,
EVER MET?
WHO IS THE BEST CELEBRITY YOU
I THINK YOU GUYS WOULD BE REAL
EVER MET?
SURPRISED IT IS BRETT
I THINK YOU GUYS WOULD BE REAL
MICHAELS.
SURPRISED IT IS BRETT
HE IS LIKE MY LEAD SINGER
MICHAELS.
POISON THE BEST CELEBRITY
HE IS LIKE MY LEAD SINGER
NUMBER ONE I MET IN MY LIFE
POISON THE BEST CELEBRITY
REALLY WELL SPOKEN, HE'S
NUMBER ONE I MET IN MY LIFE
REALLY POLITE.
REALLY WELL SPOKEN, HE'S
HE'S REALLY NICE, VERY SWEET,
REALLY POLITE.
WAS GREAT, I SPENT TIME AND
HE'S REALLY NICE, VERY SWEET,
INTERVIEWED HIM YEARS AGO.
WAS GREAT, I SPENT TIME AND
HIS DAUGHTERS IN THE NEW
INTERVIEWED HIM YEARS AGO.
SPORTS ILLUSTRATED ISSUE
HIS DAUGHTERS IN THE NEW
MAKING A LOT OF WAVES.
SPORTS ILLUSTRATED ISSUE
AND THEY ASKED HIM ABOUT THIS.
MAKING A LOT OF WAVES.
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY SHE IS
AND THEY ASKED HIM ABOUT THIS.
POSTED THIS BIKINI, AND
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY SHE IS
ANOTHER PHOTO I DECIDED NOT TO
POSTED THIS BIKINI, AND
SHOW BECAUSE IT IS KIND OF OUT
ANOTHER PHOTO I DECIDED NOT TO
THERE.
SHOW BECAUSE IT IS KIND OF OUT
AND IT IS A BIG DEAL TO BE IN
THERE.
THE SPORTS ILLUSTRATED ISSUE.
AND IT IS A BIG DEAL TO BE IN
IT IS HIS DAUGHTER THOUGH KIND
THE SPORTS ILLUSTRATED ISSUE.
OF COMING FULL CIRCLE RIGHT
IT IS HIS DAUGHTER THOUGH KIND
BECAUSE HE WAS CENTS THIS
OF COMING FULL CIRCLE RIGHT
CRAZY PARTIER BACK IN THE 80S,
BECAUSE HE WAS CENTS THIS
HE ADMITS YES IT IS FAKE
CRAZY PARTIER BACK IN THE 80S,
COMING FULL CIRCLE HERE.
HE ADMITS YES IT IS FAKE
BLEW WOULD A DAD SAY,'S DAD OF
COMING FULL CIRCLE HERE.
TWO DAUGHTERS, WHAT WOULD A
BLEW WOULD A DAD SAY,'S DAD OF
DAD SAY ABOUT THIS?
TWO DAUGHTERS, WHAT WOULD A
HE SAID HE'S PROUD OF HER.
DAD SAY ABOUT THIS?
HE'S PROUD AND I THINK BECAUSE
HE SAID HE'S PROUD OF HER.
SOME PEOPLE WERE SURPRISED
HE'S PROUD AND I THINK BECAUSE
ABOUT THAT BECAUSE HE'S
SOME PEOPLE WERE SURPRISED
EXPERIENCED IT, HE'S BEEN ON
ABOUT THAT BECAUSE HE'S
THE OTHER SIDE EVERY THINGS
EXPERIENCED IT, HE'S BEEN ON
NOW HIS DAUGHTERS POSE IN THE
THE OTHER SIDE EVERY THINGS
SPORT ILLUSTRATED BUT HE'S IN
NOW HIS DAUGHTERS POSE IN THE
SUPPORT OF T HE'S LIKE I'VE
SPORT ILLUSTRATED BUT HE'S IN
RAISED MY DAUGHTERS RIGHT.
SUPPORT OF T HE'S LIKE I'VE
I THINK THEY KNOW.
RAISED MY DAUGHTERS RIGHT.
I JUST KIND OF WANT TO KNOW
I THINK THEY KNOW.
WHAT YOU GUYS THINK ABOUT
I JUST KIND OF WANT TO KNOW
THIS, LIKE IT OR NOT?
WHAT YOU GUYS THINK ABOUT
>> NOPE.
THIS, LIKE IT OR NOT?
NOPE.
>> NOPE.
GRANTED I'M NOT BRETT
NOPE.
MICHAELS.
GRANTED I'M NOT BRETT
I HAD MY FUN, BUT DIDN'T ENDS
MICHAELS.
UP ON THE GRAM.
I HAD MY FUN, BUT DIDN'T ENDS
AND I'M HOPING MY DAUGHTER
UP ON THE GRAM.
DOESN'T EITHER IN THE PICTURES
AND I'M HOPING MY DAUGHTER
LIKE THAT, I JUST DON'T.
DOESN'T EITHER IN THE PICTURES
>> SHE'S A HOT GIRL.
LIKE THAT, I JUST DON'T.
>> YES.
>> SHE'S A HOT GIRL.
>> YOUR DAUGHTER WILL BE ON
>> YES.
THE GRAM LIKE THAT, SORRY,
>> YOUR DAUGHTER WILL BE ON
GRAM.
THE GRAM LIKE THAT, SORRY,
>> I DON'T KNOW.
GRAM.
>> ONCE SHE TURNS 18, RIGHT,
>> I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I MEAN --
>> ONCE SHE TURNS 18, RIGHT,
>> SHE CAN DO WHATEVER SHE
BUT I MEAN --
WANTS.
>> SHE CAN DO WHATEVER SHE
YOU KNOW, NOT DICTATORSHIP.
WANTS.
>> NO, THERE IS NOTHING --
YOU KNOW, NOT DICTATORSHIP.
>> BRIT'S DAD, BRIT, BRITNEY
>> NO, THERE IS NOTHING --
SPEARS, NOT BRIT MC HENRY.
>> BRIT'S DAD, BRIT, BRITNEY
AND PROBABLY BEYONCE'S DAD HAD
SPEARS, NOT BRIT MC HENRY.
T DEAL WITH THE SAME THING.
AND PROBABLY BEYONCE'S DAD HAD
SO WHAT DO YOU GUYS
There's the same old
way to get smooth,
And then there's New
Fructis Sleek Shot.
Our first
in-shower styler.
Infused with plant protein.
Just mix a shot with shampoo.
And power up with lather.
5x smoother hair.
Half the time.
It does the work for you,
So you can skip the flat iron.
Out with the old,
And in with
the smooth.
New Fructis Sleek Shot
In-Shower Styler.
By Garnier, naturally.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> NOW WE KNOW YOU GUYS
PROBABLY HAVE SO MUCH CATCHING
UP TO DO.
A LOT OF TALK.
SO WE'RE GOING TO SEND YOU OUT
TO LUNCH TOGETHER, BUT RIGHT NOW
YOU CAN READ BRANDI'S FULL STORY
IN THE MARCH ISSUE OF "REAL
SIMPLE" MAGAZINE.
>> YOU CAN WATCH THE REST OF THE
REUNION ON OUR FACEBOOK PAGE.
HAVE A GREAT DAY BECAUSE WE ARE.
YES.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪♪
Woman:
Jason Morgan?
You're Jason Morgan,
right?
Hi, I'm Harmony.
Welcome to Beechers Corners.
Thank you.
Is this
your first visit?
No.
Oh.
Well, since you called with
questions about Dawn of Day,
I suspect you want to know
what's up with us, right?
Check us out?
So, let's get to it.
♪♪
Thank you
for meeting me.
Yeah, of course.
Thanks for the...invite.
[ Sighs ]
Although I think I know
why you invited me here.
Yes.
Jason told me
about the "breakup,"
and I just wanted to offer
my support to both of you.
Which means you want to talk me
out of breaking up with him.
[ Laughs ]
-Hey.
Sorry to interrupt.
I just wanted to say "hi."
Drew. Hi.
Hi.
Hi, yourself.
Josslyn told me
the good news about Oscar...
What? What?
There's good news about Oscar?
Yeah, uh, the -- the --
the tumor hasn't grown,
so it buys him
more time.
What?
That is --
That's incredible.
Anyway, uh,
his mom and I,
we're trying to get back
to normal life.
[ Chuckles ]
Whatever that is.
So, I finally have time to check
in on Hank or Shiloh --
Shi-S-Shiloh.
No, don't --
don't even worry
about it. I got --
Well, hold on.
If -- If Drew has the time...
I mean, the more information,
the better, right?
Exactly.
And I want to help,
so...
He made a point
to be "friendly,"
so the least I could do
is be "friendly" back.
♪♪
-Hey. I-It was --
-Yeah.
It was good to see you,
and -- and I'm --
I'm really happy
to hear about Oscar.
Yeah. Me, too.
Thanks.
♪♪
Hey.
Let's hope
we get lucky
and Drew gets
leverage on Shiloh,
and then you and Jason won't
have to break up after all.
You're Dr. Neil Byrne.
And you're Alexis Davis.
♪♪
Yep.
Says it right here.
"Dr. Neil Byrne.
Psychiatrist."
Gee, I wish I had read this
before I pocketed it.
I wish I had known I was
inviting a patient to dinner.
So what do we do now?
Well, that's up to you.
♪♪
[ Dramatic music plays ]
Do you see a spot
for Kiki's memorial brick?
Yeah, near the, uh --
the flower bed down there.
She'd like that...
♪♪
If you have postmenopausal
osteoporosis
and a high risk for fracture
now might not be the best time
to ask yourself
are my bones strong?
Life is full of make-or-break
moments.
That's why it's so important
to help reduce your risk of
fracture with Prolia®.
Only Prolia® is proven to help
strengthen
and protect bones from fracture
with 1 shot every 6 months.
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take
XGEVA®.
Serious allergic reactions,
like low blood pressure; trouble
breathing;
throat tightness; face, lip, or
tongue swelling;
rash; itching; or hives have
happened.
Tell your doctor about dental
problems
as severe jaw bone problems may
happen
or new or unusual pain in your
hip groin, or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone fractures
have occurred.
Speak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects,
like low blood calcium, serious
infections,
which could need
hospitalization, skin problems,
and severe bone, joint, or
muscle pain.
Are you ready?
Ask your doctor how Prolia® can
help strengthen your bones.
In our family
we love tiny things.
We save every drop of rain,
study every bite of frost.
Because caring for tiny things
can make a mighty impact.
Ocean Spray.
Act Tiny,
Be Mighty.
Farmer Owned
Since 1930.
Don't let your longwear
weigh you down.
New Infallible Fresh Wear
Foundation by L'Oreal.
Get longwear coverage
from our most lightweight,
breathable formula.
Defies sweat and transfer.
Stays fresh. Feels light.
All day to night.
New Infallible Fresh Wear
by L'Oreal.
Oh milk. Am I willing to pay
the price for loving you?
You'll make my morning, but
ruin my day.
Complicated relationship with
milk?
Pour on the Lactaid, 100% real
milk,
just without that annoying
lactose.
Mmm, that's good.
I use this
every day
But is Beth's soap
as clean rinsing as Dove?
My soap's still leaving
plenty of things behind
But Dove is cleaner rinsing
My soap,
...Dove.
Made with 1/4
moisturizing cream...
Dove cleans and cares
beautifully.
The G.H. community
meant a lot to Kiki.
It's a very thoughtful
gesture...
♪♪
I didn't
see you there --
[ Door opens ]
Griffin?
Come away from there,
would you?
You're -- You're too close
to the edge.
You have some kind
of death wish?
Wouldn't want you
to lose your balance.
What brings you here?
Looking for Griffin?
No, I'm looking for you.
I know what you've been up to.
♪♪
We can do whatever
you feel is best...
Uh, I'm happy to give you
a referral.
Well, I can't very well
go back to Dr. Collins
because I'm representing
his wife in his divorce...
And there,
I did it again.
I offered way
too much information.
You're talking to a therapist.
There's no such thing.
But I-I can tell
you're uncomfortable.
So, I am going
to give you
the name of
an associate who may...
[ Paper tears ]
...be a good fit.
And -- And I hope
it works out
between you
and Dr. Sautner.
Thank you.
Uh, good night.
♪♪
[ Sighs ]
[ Sighing ] Oh, God.
That's a nice surprise.
Well, you know,
I had a free night.
I thought maybe we could,
uh, reconnect...
That's great, man.
Thanks, uh --
Thanks for calling.
After you.
-Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.
-[ Sighs ]
You know, I, uh...
[ Door closes ]
...really wanted to,
uh, you know,
talk about our time
in Afghanistan together.
I guess that's back when
you went by Hank, right?
[ Chuckles ]
Well, it's, uh...
it's true.
You, uh --
You saved my life.
But, uh -- But it was
more than that, man.
We, uh -- We were
seriously tight.
Although, you, uh --
you held your cards a little
closer to the vest than I did.
You sure as hell
held your liquor better.
There was, uh,
no drunken, sloppy,
late-night confessions
from you.
Take it there were
from you?
Well, you know, just things
that I had to get off my chest.
In case I didn't make it back
that day, you know?
Yeah, well,
that's understandable.
[ Chuckles ]
I mean, you always said that you
didn't remember, but, uh...
I think you were doing that
just to make me feel better.
Must have been...
some confessions.
♪♪
How are Danny
and Scout?
Scout -- she is
gonna be two...
Oh, my gosh.
...in like two weeks.
[ Laughs ]
And Danny, he's just
the sweetest,
most thoughtful little boy
in the whole entire world.
Mm.
I actually told him I was coming
here to see you and Sonny,
and -- I'm sorry, I don't have
a purse, it's in my pocket --
but he, um,
wanted me to give you this.
Oh!
[ Laughs ]
Isn't it cute?
Oh, my goodness.
It's so adorable.
[ Gasps ] Wow.
Little boys can surprise you,
can't they?
Um...
I mean,
I would never associate
Danny with
crafts and cards.
I mean, that boy, he's such
a little adventure guy.
[ Chuckling ]
Oh, tell me about it.
He's, like, running and
jumping and everything.
I know. I know. I just had
to have Monica lock the attic
because he was bringing
Annabelle the Second
up to the attic and
they were playing on the roof.
Who does that
sound like, huh?
Just like his father.
I mean, just
fearless enough
to where you want
to rip your hair out, but...
just sweet and thoughtful
all at the same time.
You're gonna have
to work a little harder
to hide how much
you love Jason
if you want to sell
this whole breakup thing.
But before I answer
your questions,
do you mind answering
one of mine?
Uh, depends
on the question.
You're here
on someone's behalf.
Who?
A family member?
I consider her one,
yes.
In Beechers Corners?
Is it someone I know?
No.
Well, then,
why come here?
Why not just talk to Shiloh?
He's in Port Charles.
Because I wanted to talk
to someone besides...
Hank Archer.
[ Laughs ]
Now that's a blast
from the past.
[ Chuckles ]
I used to be
called Lorraine.
Yeah, me,
a "Lorraine."
My parents chose it,
obviously,
but it was
never a good fit.
I found it so freeing
and empowering
to be able to choose
my own name.
So, you became Harmony.
Like Hank became Shiloh.
Well, choosing my own name
was a-a bridge
to becoming my true self.
Shiloh.
[ Chuckles ]
He untethered me from
what was holding me back,
and Dawn of Day
opened my mind
and my heart
to my own potential.
♪♪
Did you notice that community
center across the street?
Shiloh and I built it
from the ground up.
Are you still in touch
with, uh -- with Shiloh?
Yeah, well...of course.
We still conduct business
together,
if that's what you mean.
But you're not together.
I mean, you're here.
Shiloh's in Port Charles.
Why?
♪♪
MOVING?
THAT'S HARDER NOW BECAUSE
OF PSORIATIC ARTHRITIS.
BUT YOU'RE STILL MOVED
BY MOMENTS LIKE THIS.
DON'T LET PSORIATIC
ARTHRITIS TAKE THEM AWAY.
TALTZ REDUCES JOINT
PAIN AND STIFFNESS
AND HELPS STOP THE
PROGRESSION OF JOINT DAMAGE.
FOR PEOPLE WITH
MODERATE TO
SEVERE PSORIASIS,
90% SAW SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT.
TALTZ EVEN GIVES YOU A CHANCE
AT COMPLETELY
CLEAR SKIN.
DON'T USE IF YOU'RE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING, YOU SHOULD
BE CHECKED FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR
ABILITY TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU
HAVE AN INFECTION, SYMPTOMS,
OR RECEIVED A
VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INFLAMMATORY BOWEL DISEASE
CAN HAPPEN WITH TALTZ,
INCLUDING WORSENING OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
FOR ALL THE THINGS
THAT MOVE YOU.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
Gentle means everything,
so we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients
Added one handed pumps
And beat the
top safety standards
The new JOHNSON'S®
Choose Gentle
This is nice.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is nice.
Mmmm how did you make the
dip so rich and creamy?
Oh, it's a Philadelphia-
-Family Recipe.
Can I see it?
No.
New Philadelphia Dips.
So good,
you'll take all the credit.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Voluptuous Volume.
Intense Length.
Feathery-Soft Lashes.
This is what
paradise looks like.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Take your lashes to paradise.
90% of women
have a skincare routine.
But what about a
lip care routine?
Pay your lips some attention.
The ChapStick Total
Hydration Collection.
Exfoliate
Nourish
Naturally enhance
your lips.
ChapStick.
Put your lips first.
You can't put a price on love.
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
Ever notice how hard it is to
clean impossible kitchen and
bathroom messes with wipes
and spray cleaners?
Try Mr. Clean Magic Eraser.
Just add water, squeeze,
and erase.
Mr. Clean Magic Eraser works
great
on burnt-on food in the
kitchen.
It's perfect for cleaning
stubborn bathroom soap scum.
Even on glass.
And it even removes four times
more permanent marker per swipe.
Try Mr. Clean Magic Eraser,
for your impossible kitchen and
bathroom messes.
Emerge Restored,
Replenished,
Fortified.
Emerge everyday with Emergen-C.
Packed with B vitamins,
Electrolytes, Antioxidants,
Plus more vitamin C than
10 oranges.
Why not feel this good
every day?
Emerge and See.
I don't understand. What is it
you think I'm "up to"?
Oh, come on, Kevin. It's why
you're up here, isn't it?
I went to your office,
looking for you.
I found this
on your desk.
♪♪
You've arranged for
a commemorative brick
in Kiki's honor.
The letter says that
the best way to choose a spot
is to look down
from the roof,
so I-I came up here
to see for myself,
give you my input...
It's a lovely gesture, Kevin.
Thank you.
It's all
I could think of.
Just have something of Kiki
here at the hospital,
and maybe bring
some small comfort
to the people
who miss her.
I was just saying
the same thing.
Let me know when, uh,
you guys pick the final spot.
I'm sorry.
I, uh...
I have somewhere
I need to be.
♪♪
Now Kiki will be
a part of the place
that she loved forever.
I admit,
a brick isn't much,
but if it dissipates
your anger towards me,
then I'm doubly glad
I thought of it.
I'm not angry, Kevin.
I jumped to conclusions.
I owe you an apology.
♪♪
See, in order to find out
more about Shiloh,
I have to make myself
seem really vulnerable.
Okay, but this guy
obviously has charisma,
and he knows
how to use it...
Do you think
he's a sexual predator?
Well, I intend
to find out.
Not only
for Kristina's sake,
but every other girl
that's living under that roof.
That's why I have
to see this through.
Okay. But to do that,
you have to con him, right?
Do you think you can?
Trust me.
Shiloh's about to get
a taste of his own medicine.
I was one of Shiloh's
earliest supporters.
He was the visionary,
and I was the pragmatist
to help make it work.
So, why are
you guys apart?
That's simple -- he wants
to expand the work that we do.
Okay,
so why Port Charles?
Well, the city suffered
a bad earthquake a while back,
and Shiloh found people
in Port Charles
who needed
the kind of outreach
that Dawn of Day
could provide.
So, he left,
and I stayed behind
to continue the work
that we do here.
Yeah, he seems, uh,
pretty devoted to his work.
What about a life
outside of it?
Shiloh's life
is his work.
Oh, so no -- no family?
No -- No interest in --
in having a family?
[ Chuckles ]
Dawn of Day is a family.
Why do you ask?
Well, because [sighs]
the young lady
I'm here for,
I mean, she's really involved
with Dawn of Day,
but she's -- you know,
she's a little naive,
and she's growing
attached to Shiloh
as more than a mentor.
I'm s--
What are you implying?
She's falling for him.
So, h-how does he --
how does he handle
situations like this
when they come up?
♪♪
Yeah, well, that's the, uh --
the thing about confessions.
When you're in the middle
of making them,
they seem of
monumental importance.
But, uh, when you're
looking at them in the
grand scheme of life,
well, they're not important
at all, are they?
I guess you got a point,
but, uh, you know,
why are you still
thinking about them?
I don't know. I mean, I guess
coming back to Port Charles,
it just, you know, brought it
all back, you know?
First,
I run into a brother
that I didn't even know you have
with your face.
Yeah.
Right? And then
I-I see you again
with -- with --
with a-another face,
and -- and you don't know me
from Adam, you know, so...
Well, I don't remember
anyone or anything,
so, uh, don't take it
personally.
Not at all.
So, is there any chance
your memories will return?
♪♪
-We're doing karaoke later,
and you're gonna sing.
-Jamie, this is your house?
-I know, it's not much,
but it's home.
Right, kids?
-Kids?
-Papa, Papa!
-[ Laughs ]
-You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
-Oh, yeah.
-This one is tiny like a child.
-Yeah, she is.
Oh, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most --
a home and auto bundle
from Progressive.
-Oh, sweetie,
please, play for us.
-Oh, no, I couldn't.
-Please.
-Okay.
[ Singing in Spanish ]
There's little rest
for a single dad,
and back pain made it hard to
sleep and get up on time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid,
plus the 12 hour pain
relieving strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a Better AM.
This is Charlie not coughing
because he took Delsym 12-hour.
And this is Charlie still not
coughing
while trying his hardest not to
wake Zeus.
Delsym 12-hour.
Nothing lasts
longer for powerful
cough relief.
Advanced Génifique Serum
activates signs
of youthful-looking skin.
Fine lines appear reduced.
Skin is more radiant,
looks visibly younger
in only four weeks.
Love Your Age.
Customize your
free gift at Macy's.
The Beauty Destination.
At Children's National,
Customize your
free gift at Macy's.
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
[phone ringing]
Remember the way we
used to do things?
Hey man...
Like connect with friends?
Dig it!
Or get in shape?
Or sell a house
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
[crash]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
♪ Keep your feet
from coming off the ground ♪
[ Clanging ]
[ Wrench clatters ]
♪♪
♪ Step in line and move along ♪
[ Grunts ]
♪ I said, all right,
I'm getting home ♪
♪ We paint a line ♪
♪ And set the course ♪
[ Knock on door ]
♪ We pass on by
and through the door ♪
♪ And the thought
occurs to me ♪
Sasha.
Mind if I come in?
Uh, sure.
♪♪
I was in town visiting Nina
and thought I'd stop by.
I hope
that's all right.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Uh...
It's been a while.
Not since
Kiki's funeral...
♪ Keep your feet
from coming off the ground ♪
I can't imagine what
you've been going through.
♪ Live each moment ♪
It must be so hard walking past
Kiki's apartment every day...
How are you doing?
♪ Take it in
before it turns to memory ♪
Want to know
how I'm doing?
I'm sick and tired
of everybody talking to me
about Kiki.
Talking isn't gonna
bring her back.
♪ Don't get lost
and lose the here ♪
Once I calmed down,
I realized --
that you weren't
protecting Franco.
You didn't notify the
police because you knew
he wasn't a threat,
and if you thought he was, you
definitely would've warned us.
I never believed
Franco would harm anyone.
Especially not
your beautiful daughter...
Even with
his dark side,
I never thought he would act
on those impulses.
I know.
I spoke with him.
I'm convinced
he's innocent.
That means the killer
is still free.
That is a real problem.
Doesn't have to be.
You need to go
to the police, Kevin.
You need to tell them that
they have the wrong man.
[ Knock on door ]
Come in.
You know, I've thought about it,
and I thought, "You know what?
I've already spilled my guts
to you."
And -- And since
I'm perfectly at ease
talking to a complete stranger,
which I have no explanation for,
it makes sense that I
would be comfortable
speaking to you here.
So, if you're still
willing to treat me...
I am.
And based on
our previous discussion,
you have some intriguing
issues to work out.
Uh...referring back
to our conversation,
I-I just have to ask,
just to be sure...
When we met
at Charlie's,
did you know that
I was your patient?
♪♪
So, supposedly,
there's a procedure
that could, um
[inhales deeply]
possibly undo
what had been done to me.
Well, forgive me, I-I-I don't
know what happened to you.
Long story.
Heard plenty of
"long stories," brother.
[ Laughs ]
Yeah, not like this,
I can assure you.
You know how, um...
you said you were surprised
to hear that I went AWOL?
Yeah.
Well, that wasn't
the case.
I was abducted.
I knew it.
I knew it. I knew you would
never abandon your post.
That's what happened
to you...
Well, the plan
was to, uh...
put me in
my brother's place to, uh...
transfer his knowledge,
his memories into my head,
and then
he could be eliminated.
Yeah, but he's still
around, so...
someone messed up.
First part worked.
I got his memories,
and, uh, well, I lost my own.
Now, you said that
there was some procedure
that could help
you recover your memories.
Now, why -- why --
why wouldn't you do that?
What -- What could be
holding you back?
♪♪
Maybe Sonny could persuade
Shiloh to leave town?
No, no, no, no, no.
No,
that could backfire.
Shiloh could
tell Kristina.
Kristina -- she could dig in
so much harder.
No way.
All right.
Oh, I hate this.
I hate this
for everyone.
You and Jason just
got back together.
I'd like to wring
Shiloh's enlightened neck.
I've got to pretend
to hang on to his every word.
God.
Yeah.
What if he catches on
that you're playing him?
Well, I've -- I-I-I have
thought about this,
and I've got a few things
going for me.
One: I am
an experienced con.
Two: Shiloh expects women
to fall for him,
including Kristina.
I mean, and
all these other girls,
they're almost like
his groupies,
and he assumes
he can pull me in.
All I have to do
is play along.
Shiloh is naturally warm
and inclusive,
and that can be misunderstood
by some of our more...
vulnerable volunteers.
So, what does Shiloh do
about that?
He handles it.
He handles it?
I-I mean,
like I said,
my friend's vulnerable
and -- and naive.
I just -- I don't --
I don't want her to get hurt,
so, I mean, what d--
how does he handle --
Cop Billy: Jason Morgan?
Yeah. Um...
is there --
is there a problem?
Ran your plates.
Seems you have an arrest record
here in Beechers Corners.
For murder.
Yeah, those --
those charges were dropped.
Yes, I know, but you're on
the wrong side of the law again.
♪♪
Dove Intensive Repair
conditioner proves it can.
We treat one brush
with Dove conditioner...
...and expose both
to heat styling, ...
...to bleaching...
...and even coloring.
The difference is clear.
The brush treated with Dove
is visibly smoother....
...and protected against damage.
♪♪
Dove Intensive Repair
conditioner.
For 100% touchably
beautiful hair.
Since one conditioner
doesn't fit all.
Dove Ultra-Care Conditioners.
♪ They say quit
they say done ♪
♪ They say we're
too grown for fun ♪
♪ They say old,
we say young ♪
♪ We say playful's never done ♪
♪ Don't fight the feeling
just let it flow ♪
♪ Stack it up,
rack it up, let it go ♪
♪ Laughter is calling
pick up the phone ♪
♪ Let's stay playful, Oreo ♪
Hello?
Psych!
♪ If we're still smiling
the future's bueno ♪
♪ I got a secret
the world should know ♪
♪ Let's stay playful, Oreo ♪
♪
Real cheese people are
ham and swiss people.
They're hot and cold.
Big and bold.
But they would never
make a sandwich
with pasteurized
process cheese food.
Sargento slices are 100%
real, natural cheese.
Sargento,
we're real
cheese people.
Stand up to Chronic
Migraine with BOTOX®.
What if you had fewer headaches
and migraines a month?
BOTOX® prevents
headaches and migraines
before they even start.
BOTOX® is for adults
with Chronic Migraine,
15 or more headache
days a month,
each lasting 4 hours or more.
BOTOX® injections take about
15 mins. in your doctor's office
and are covered
by most insurance.
Effects of BOTOX® may spread
hours to weeks after injection
causing serious symptoms.
Alert your doctor right away,
as difficulty swallowing,
speaking, breathing,
eye problems,
or muscle weakness
can be signs of a
life-threatening condition.
Side effects may
include allergic reactions,
neck and injection site pain,
fatigue, and headache.
Don't receive BOTOX® if
there's a skin infection.
Tell your doctor your
medical history, muscle or
nerve conditions,
and medications,
including botulinum toxins,
as these may increase the
risk of serious side effects.
With the BOTOX® Savings Program,
most people with
commercial insurance
pay nothing out of pocket.
Talk to your doctor and visit
BOTOXChronicMigraine.com
to enroll.
It's your weekend to save,
during Pier 1's storewide
Presidents Day Sale.
February 14th through the 18th.
Get up to $100 off
our most loved items.
Get started on
your spring refresh
with big savings this weekend.
In store and at pier1.com.
♪ I'M A BIG KID NOW ♪
♪ WENT FROM BABY BOTTLES TO
DRINKING FROM SIPPY CUPS ♪
♪ WENT FROM WEARING DIAPERS TO
ROCKING THESE FRESH PULL-UPS ♪
♪ WE'RE 50 MILLION STRONG ♪
♪ SO PUT ON YOUR PULL-UPS
AND HELP US SING THIS SONG ♪
You called to make
this appointment at
5:00 this afternoon.
At which time, I was already
sitting down at Charlie's
with my book
and my coffee.
So, no -- I didn't know
that the interesting woman
sitting down next to me --
and who I asked to dinner --
was Alexis Davis,
my soon-to-be patient.
And if I did,
I would never
have asked you to dinner.
I apologize for questioning
your professionalism.
Apology accepted.
But, you know,
if we move forward...
can you trust me?
Now, see, there's a lot
to unpack in that question.
Hmm.
I can try.
Well, why don't we, um,
see how today goes,
and if you choose to,
we can continue?
Okay.
♪♪
You were, uh, prompted
to call me this afternoon,
and I'm just wondering
why it was so urgent
to return to therapy
at this point.
Oh, well, there are
a lot of reasons.
Chief among them
i-is the feeling I had
when I saw my ex-husband
kissing his girlfriend,
his new girlfriend.
And then there was yesterday,
I had this experience
at this organization
called Dawn of Day.
♪♪
So, as I
understand it, uh...
the procedure is a lot like
overwriting a computer program.
Yeah.
My old memories
will be restored --
but all the memories I've made
in the past five years
would essentially be eliminated,
deleted.
You know...
The relationships I've made,
people I've grown to love,
memories of
my daughter, Scout.
From the day she was born
up until now, gone.
Hmm.
I didn't even know
I had a son
until I moved
to Port Charles,
so meeting him,
the memories
we've made together...
I'd lose them.
♪♪
They mean
everything to me.
So...
The short answer
is "no."
I will not be having
the procedure.
That's good.
That's good, man. You got
your priorities straight.
[ Chuckles ]
You know the worst part
of this whole thing
is having
to lie to Danny.
I know, he's just
too young to understand
everything
that's going on,
and I know he's gonna be
missing out
on some major
family time.
Can't you guys meet up
at the Quartermaines?
Well, yeah, I'm --
I'm counting on it.
Monica's been
pretty great about that.
She's the ultimate
hands-off mother-in-law.
Monica?
Yeah.
A-Are you serious?
Oh, my gosh,
when I was married to A.J.,
all she did was meddle.
I mean,
I guess I understand,
because A.J. and I loathed
each other, but...
Anyway, I'm just saying,
you guys have a totally
different relationship
than I had.
You know, it's --
it's really funny.
For two people that
can't stand each other,
you two are a lot alike...
In what universe?
You both have
a love for family.
Well, you're a part
of that club, too, Sam.
I mean, look at
everything you're doing
to protect Kristina.
Yeah, but I also
know what it's like
to have a guy use you
and make you
feel worthless
and tear down
your self-esteem.
And I am not gonna let Shiloh
do that to Kristina.
Officer, I've done
nothing wrong.
I'm just trying to sit here
and have a conversation...
Could there be some
kind of mistake?
No mistake.
Mr. Morgan's vehicle
is parked too close to
a designated handicapped spot.
Th-There was no --
There was no sign.
They're difficult to see,
even in the daylight.
I need you to move it now,
or I'll have it impounded.
It's okay, Billy.
Billy.
Mr. Morgan will move
his car shortly. Okay?
We're just wrapping
things up here.
But thank you
for your diligence.
[ Sighs ]
Sure thing, Harmony.
Okay.
♪♪
I'm sorry.
His bark is worse
than his bite.
Yeah, well, thank you
for smoothing that over.
Yeah.
It's wonderful
how this community
looks out
for each other.
It's really come together
since Dawn of Day launched here.
I hope we can bring
that same sort of fellowship
to Port Charles.
Is there anything else
you'd like to know?
I think
I've heard enough.
I hope I've calmed
your anxieties
on behalf
of your...person.
Do you feel more comfortable
about Dawn of Day now?
I've learned a lot.
Look, I-I-I'm sorry.
Really, I-I-I don't know
what came over me.
It's just...
Look, I don't know
what's worse --
thinking about Kiki,
or -- or -- or
not thinking about her.
I-I'm consumed
with missing her.
I-I can't seem to find
a moment's peace.
So, how did you
get those bruises?
I noticed them
when I came in.
Did you get mugged
or something?
Uh...boxing.
I-I spar sometimes.
With those neurosurgeon hands?
Are you crazy?
No, we, uh --
we wear gloves.
You know, big --
big, padded ones.
Okay, well, pick someone
your own size next time.
[ Chuckles ] Looks like
you were boxing a kangaroo.
No, I just, uh...
I just lost focus,
that's all.
I...
My mind wanders, and, uh,
regret just takes over.
I know the feeling.
What do you
have to regret?
♪♪
It's important
that the police
stop wasting their time
on Franco --
and -- and find
the monster who killed Kiki.
I know you're struggling
with terrible grief,
and I didn't want to add to it
by upsetting you...
You didn't. It's -- It isn't
your fault that I overreacted.
But you ran
right back to Griffin.
[ Chuckles ] What?
Oh, you saw Griffin
comforting me
and you assumed that
I went back to him?
Ava, you ran out on me.
And you're
so beautiful, and...
Come on.
Let's face it --
the man's an Adonis,
and...
Naturally, I just
thought that --
You --
You're insane.
You know that?
And I'd have to be equally
insane to go back to the man
who betrayed me
with my own daughter.
Kevin...
[ Chuckling ] Oh, Kevin.
♪♪
The Russells travel to a
different swim meet every
Saturday.
But now... it's Thursday.
Good thing they discovered Gain
Flings.
The only detergent with
concentrated Gain,
Oxi Boost, and Febreze Odor
Remover.
Mmhmm. Smelling is believing.
And Gain Flings can HIYA Karate
stink too.
Try new improved Gain Flings.
Not having a good breakfast
can make you feel
like your day never started.
Get going with Carnation
Breakfast Essentials®.
It has protein,
plus 21 vitamins
and minerals
including calcium
and vitamin D,
to help your family
be their best.
Carnation Breakfast
Essentials®.
Searching for a way to
help stop your cold sore?
t Only Abreva canly
get rid of it in...
...as little as 2 1/2 days
when used at the first sign.
Abreva starts to
work immediately
to block the virus and
protect healthy cells.
Abreva acts on it.
So you can too.
♪ I'M A BIG KID NOW ♪
♪ WENT FROM BABY BOTTLES TO
DRINKING FROM SIPPY CUPS ♪
♪ WENT FROM WEARING DIAPERS TO
ROCKING THESE FRESH PULL-UPS ♪
♪ WE'RE 50 MILLION STRONG ♪
♪ SO PUT ON YOUR PULL-UPS
AND HELP US SING THIS SONG ♪
Gentle means everything,
so we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients
Added one handed pumps
And beat the
top safety standards
The new JOHNSON'S®
Choose Gentle
I'm a fighter.
Always have been.
When I found out I had
Age-related Macular
Degeneration,
AMD,
I wanted to fight back.
My doctor and I came up
with a plan.
It includes
PreserVision.
Only PreserVision
AREDS 2
has the exact
nutrient formula
recommended by the
National Eye Institute
to help reduce the risk
of progression of moderate
to advanced AMD.
That's why I fight.
Because it's
my vision.
PreserVision.
Also, in a great-tasting
chewable.
(coughs)
Hi Susan!
Honey? I respect that.
But that cough looks
pretty bad...
try this NEW Robitussin Honey.
The real honey you love...
Plus the powerful cough
relief you need.
Mind if I root through
your trash?
New Robitussin Honey.
Because it's never just a cough.
Allergies with sinus
congestion and pressure?
You won't find relief here.
Go to the pharmacy counter
for powerful Claritin-D.
While the leading allergy spray
only relieves 6 symptoms,
Claritin-D relieves 8, including
sinus congestion and pressure.
Claritin-D relieves more.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
[ Sighs ]
I-I came to Port Charles
with zero expectations.
I was gonna blow in,
meet my biological mother,
and blow out.
And then I met Nina,
and Kiki, and Charlotte,
and all these people that
I came to care about.
And I found myself
worrying about you all,
hoping that
you were all okay.
That's good.
[ Chuckles ]
That's --
That's a good thing.
You made --
You made connections.
I just want
to do the right thing,
but I'm not sure how.
There are things that are
[exhales sharply]
hard to fix.
♪♪
You want
to talk about it?
I'm, uh -- I'm open,
wide-open
to distractions, um...
And I-I really
want to help.
Thanks.
♪♪
[ Chuckles ]
Why is it so hot in here?
It's the building.
You can't -- You can't
control the radiator.
Kiki showed me
a few tricks,
but I never really
got the hang of it.
You know, she had
the -- the magic touch...
♪♪
...with everything
she did.
[ Sighs ]
Are you okay?
I really thought
I had lost you.
[ Exhales sharply ]
You know...
it's only been a short time,
Ava, but...
you have my heart.
[ Chuckles ]
You're everything
to me.
I don't think
I'd be able to go on
putting one foot in front
of the other if I --
if I'd lost
the woman I love.
♪♪
You...
You love me?
In an effort to try to
heal this rift between
my daughter and me,
I agreed
to attend a seminar
led by this man
that she respects.
And how was it?
Weird.
Completely uncomfortable,
but I played nicely in order
to appease my daughter,
and in that,
I ended up admitting
that I have this yearning
to have the same feeling
that I had when I was
with my ex.
And as you astutely
put it,
y-you said that
I tend to "frame everything
in -- in the context
of my ex,"
and I-I-I don't want
to do that anymore.
Um...
I'm, uh, fairly certain
that I don't want a relationship
with him again.
However, his type,
that type is the type
that I am, uh, drawn to.
So, you have a type?
Oh, I do.
I do, yes. Um...
Um, Dangerous.
Selfish.
Incapable of intimacy
and honesty, and...
someone who loves power more
than they will ever love me.
Is there a man
in your life
who, uh, set this pattern
up for you?
My father.
You know,
it's a small world,
because he's one of those
exiled Russian aristocrats
that you're so fond
of studying.
Hmm.
Shiloh:
That is a lot of pain that
you're carrying around, man.
And if you ever
just want to reconcile
what happened to you
or -- or just vent...
my seminars have helped ease
a lot of suffering.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Including your own?
Well, they're a result
of my own breakthroughs,
you know?
Hmm.
I've learned to untie
from my troubled past.
And now that I know that it's
no longer burdening you, either,
well, looks like we both
could have a little closure.
Tell you what.
No charge.
[ Chuckles ]
Hell, maybe I should
start my own seminars.
♪♪
Looks like you've given me
my life back yet again.
Thank you.
Okay.
All right.
♪♪
Thanks for coming by, man.
It was good seeing you.
Thanks for having me.
Anytime.
♪♪
I'd invite you
to attend an open house
here or
in Port Charles,
but something tells me
that'll never happen.
You know, I really wish you'd
open your mind and accept help.
You must bear scars
being arrested
for a murder that
you didn't commit.
No. I don't.
Thank you for your time.
♪♪
Okay, I-I know that
you and Jason aren't
candy-hearts-and-flowers
kind of people,
but you should be together
on Valentine's Day.
I have plans
You're going to that event
at Dawn of Day, aren't you?
I've seen the fliers --
"True Love Begins
with Self Love."
[ Laughs ]
Shiloh's expecting me.
Ugh, well, you can
have an emergency.
You know, a tire could blow,
anything.
Oh, God.
No, no, no, no.
That is very tempting.
Don't do that.
I will not be spending
Valentine's Day
with the man
that I love.
I will be at
the Dawn of Day house,
soaking up
all of Shiloh's...
wisdom with an eager smile
on my face.
Because the harder
I sell this...
the faster I can
get Kristina out of there.
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
Does removing makeup
feel like this?
Your skin deserves better.
Garnier Micellar Cleansing Water
with micelles that
work like a magnet.
It's a pure way to remove
stubborn makeup
without harsh rubbing.
Cleansing, reinvented.
Micellar Water.
By Garnier,
Naturally!
This time, it's his turn.
You have 4.3 minutes
to yourself.
This calls for a
taste of cheesecake.
Philadelphia Cheesecake Cups.
Rich, creamy cheesecake
with real strawberries.
Find them with the
refrigerated desserts.
At last, one red that works on
everyone.
New Made for All lip color from
Maybelline New York.
Tested on 50 skin tones.
Sensational on all.
New Made for All.
Only from Maybelline New York.
♪
Cats will do anything
for the irresistible taste of
TEMPTATIONS™ treats.
What are you doing?
Oh hey, check this out.
TEMPTATIONS ™.
All
It Takes
Is A Shake™.
(Thunderclap)
If your day doesn't
unfold as predicted.
Unfold this.
New Neutrogena®
Makeup Remover single.
And remove 99% of makeup.
100% rain or shine.
Neutrogena®.
Announcing our Biggest Event
Ever.
More ways to save on brands
you love.
More furniture.
More rugs...
Lamps...
Art.
Come in for huge savings,
right now.
Go finding today. HomeGoods.
You can't put a price on love.
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
>> TECH: At Safelite AutoGlass
we know that when you're
spending time with the grandkids
every minute counts.
And you don't have time
for a cracked windshield.
That's why we
show you exactly
when we'll be there.
Saving you time, so you
can keep saving the world.
>> KIDS: ♪ Safelite repair,
Safelite replace ♪
The day after chemo
shouldn't mean going
back to the doctor
just for a shot.
With Neulasta Onpro
patients get their day back...
to be with family,
or just to sleep in.
Strong chemo can put you at
risk of serious infection.
In a key study Neulasta
reduced the risk of infection
from 17% to 1%,
a 94% decrease.
Neulasta Onpro is designed
to deliver Neulasta
the day after chemo
and is used by most patients
today.
Neulasta is for certain
cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta if you're
allergic to it
or Neupogen (filgrastim).
An incomplete dose could
increase infection risk.
Ruptured spleen,
sometimes fatal as well as
serious lung problems,
allergic reactions,
kidney injuries and capillary
leak syndrome have occurred.
Report abdominal or shoulder
tip pain, trouble breathing
or allergic reactions to
your doctor right away.
In patients with sickle
cell disorders,
serious, sometimes fatal crises
can occur.
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
Ask your doctor about
Neulasta Onpro.
Pay no more than $5 per dose
with copay card.
So, if it's okay with you,
I think maybe we could skip over
the gory details
of my family,
because if we go through
all the twists and turns,
we're gonna be here
all year, right?
So, if I can
just sum it all up by saying
that my father was...
distant, unapproachable,
and a controlling figure
in my life.
He was, um...ruthless,
and powerful,
and I was simultaneously
drawn to him
and repelled by him.
I rarely got
his attention,
and I never earned
his love...
Which would explain
why I've had
a string of
hideous relationships
with ruthless
and unattainable men.
You mentioned earning
your father's love.
Yeah, that's not your job
to earn your father's love.
Parental love is a gift --
no strings attached.
Then you don't know
my family,
because in my family,
love is not a gift.
It's a weakness
to be exploited.
And at what age
did you realize that?
Oh. Well,
I have no idea,
because I've blocked out
most of my childhood.
Did I mention that my stepmother
murdered my mother --
and I witnessed it?
♪♪
Um, you probably have suffered
some, uh, post-traumatic stress.
Have you ever been
diagnosed or treated?
No.
So, uh, where does
your father fit in here?
Well, he was the only one
that would --
could check
my stepmother,
because he was as ruthless
and cruel as she was.
So perhaps you equate cruelty
and ruthlessness to safety.
Only powerful men --
as selfish
and unattainable
as they are --
assure you
your survival.
♪♪
You know, I-I never really
thought about it like that.
Well...
[ Notebook thuds ]
...if we decide
to move forward,
we can help you
lead yourself
to a better understanding
of yourself.
Start guiding you away
from the people
that are not good for you
or to you,
and maybe lead you
to healthier relationships.
I think I'd like that.
So, another appointment?
Yeah.
I was hoping to save those words
for Valentine's Day.
Don't.
Please.
I won't.
♪♪
I love you.
I love you, too.
I love you very much.
♪♪
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to
bring up Kiki again for you...
I really should be
heading out...
Uh, thank you
for stopping by.
If I come back,
I'll bring ice packs.
[ Chuckles ] You're welcome
to stop by anytime.
Just, um...
do me a favor --
work on those regrets.
You're just too young to have
that weighing on you.
So are you.
♪♪
Harmony.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
You sound upbeat.
Well, it is a beautiful night.
And I have just discovered
that a potential threat
isn't so threatening at all.
Well, I thought
you should know...
I just met with
a Jason Morgan.
He was questioning me
about you.
Yeah, yeah, I expected that.
What's the upshot?
I arranged for an assist
from our favorite cop Billy.
Oh, wonderful.
Well, I hope he made Jason
feel less than welcome.
No, Billy did his part.
Jason didn't seem
to be intimidated,
but I doubt he'll be back
in Beechers Corners.
He didn't learn anything
we didn't want him to know.
That's good.
♪♪
Hey!
You just missed Sam.
Or was that intentional?
Uh, one of your --
one of your bartenders
is into Dawn of Day.
What?
Which one?
No idea --
Sonny was talking to him.
Damn it.
I mean,
I can't fire him.
But I also don't want him
here lurking around,
reporting everything
back to Shiloh.
I really wanted this to be
a safe place for you and Sam.
It's okay, Carly. We'll f--
We'll find a safe place.
[ Sighs ]
I can't tell you
how unsettling it is
that this Shiloh guy
was able to make inroads for
a long time and no one noticed.
[ Sighs ]
Do you know that
Dawn of Day was behind
the clothing drive that the kids
were a part of last fall?
Mm-hmm.
Had I known that, I would have
never let Josslyn participate!
Okay, okay,
Josslyn is not vulnerable.
She has a great sense
of herself...
Okay, it's Kristina.
She's the one who's in deep.
Really?
Okay, do you think Sam's gonna
be able to pull her out?
I don't know.
It might --
It might help
if Shiloh's distracted.
You know, feeling a little
pressure from the outside.
What kind of pressure?
I'm not sure.
I took a trip up
to Beechers Corners
to check out
the original Dawn of Day,
and it did give me a good idea
of how it works.
But now...
I got to figure out
how to take it down.
into each dish.
That's what my food is about--
flavor, love.
Whew!
Do-or-die time.
I'm ready.
I've been ready.
I need everybody
to kind of start
setting up
their stations, okay?
ARIEL: You guys should be doing
last-minute things right now.
MOTTO: How are we looking
on apps over there, Kanae?
I still got to push out
all these dumplings,
'cause if I don't get them
done now, it's gonna be hell.
MIA: Communicate, okay?
ALL: Yes.
Come on, guys,
let's do a little group huddle.
Please,
always communication,
appetizers, appetizers,
communicate.
I'm gonna talk you guys
through this.
I'm never gonna leave
you alone, all right?
I'm gonna make sure
you guys are okay
the whole step of the way.
I want you supporting him.
When I call the meats,
pull the meats,
and then just help him
whenever possible.
On three, "A-Team."
One, two, three...
ALL: A-Team!
-Let's go. Let's do this.
GORDON: Mia, one final thing.
Ariel, let's go.
Every night when we are ready,
what's the one thing
I do to Marino?
ARIEL: Oh, tell him
to open Hell's Kitchen.
-So can you do it together?
-Together? Yes.
-On the count of three...
-Off you go.
BOTH: One, two, three...
Marino,
open Hell's Kitchen!
Subito.
♪ ♪
NARRATOR: Hell's Kitchen
is the place to be
for this
much-anticipated showdown
between veteran Ariel
and rookie Mia.
Of course the finalists'
families are in attendance...
-To our baby.
-She is our baby.
NARRATOR:
Along with other VIPs.
In Ariel's kitchen, former
O.J. Simpson prosecutor
Marcia Clark will be dining.
Please let me introduce you
to our finalist, Ariel.
Hi. Welcome.
Pleasure to have you
-this evening.
-Thank you.
NARRATOR: While Mia's kitchen
will host actor
and comedian J.B. Smoove.
Wow, bro, this is the joint.
Look at this, man.
Okay, guys, listen up.
Two risotto, one shrimp scampi,
one ceviche.
ALL: Heard.
-Thank you.
MIA: This is it.
It's crunch time.
I have to prove
that I have it in me
to lead an entire kitchen,
and I feel like I'm gonna
surprise Chef Ramsay
with my performance tonight.
How long--two risotto,
shrimp, ceviche?
-Six minutes.
-Heard that.
-Risotto working.
JOSE: Putting Trev on apps,
you know, I would have
went a different route.
That was Mia's decision,
but, you know,
you don't want to start off
slow 'cause then it could
just slow down
the whole service after that.
-Risotto, 30 seconds.
-Okay.
-30 seconds.
-Are you tasting it?
Yes, I'm tasting everything.
More salt.
-More salt. Heard, Chef.
-Mm-hmm.
Season every stage,
every stage.
TREV: Yes, Chef.
-Mia on it, man.
Trev,
I don't need this, dude.
Come on, like,
this is rookie [bleep].
This needs to be perfect.
Walking risotto.
Good job.
Keep it coming, okay?
-Got it.
-Good girl.
Go.
Trev, taste it.
Tasting everything, Chef.
All right, listen up,
Red Team.
-You guys ready for this?
ALL: Yes, Chef.
All right,
we have a four-top,
away--two scallops,
two dumplings.
ALL: Heard, Chef.
ARIEL: My team is amped up.
They are in this,
and I feel like we're gonna
just knock this
out of the park tonight.
KANAE: Scotley, five minutes
all day, okay?
Five minutes, heard.
KANAE: We only have
one shot at tonight,
and we are determined
to have everything
come out perfect for Ariel.
[bleep], Motto, it burnt.
Huh?
-They burnt.
-[bleep].
This is not going
according to plan.
Kanae, get it together.
You got this, baby.
ARIEL: Are we walking two
dumplings with two scallops?
MOTTO: Yes, Chef.
-Yes, right after.
SCOTLEY:
Walking scallops.
ARIEL: Dumplings, let's go.
KANAE: I need 30 seconds, Chef,
and it will be at the window.
Ariel, I've got scallops dying.
We've got to go.
We can't just leave food
hanging like that.
This is your standards.
All right,
I need those two dumplings.
-Let's go, guys.
KANAE: Yes, Chef.
♪ ♪
I need service, please.
Thank God.
I didn't make all these
damn dumplings for nothing.
Rock that [bleep].
NARRATOR: With Kanae's
quick recovery on dumplings...
Thank you, and ceviche
right behind it, please.
NARRATOR: Appetizers
are now making their way
out of both kitchens.
Table 23--this is my family,
VIP, please.
Thank you so much.
-Like mami.
BOTH: Bon appétit.
NARRATOR: And receiving
high praise from the diners.
BOTH: Mmm.
That's phenomenal.
Wow.
-It's pretty damn good.
This risotto is definitely
off the hook.
Fire two sea bass,
two pork.
Two sea bass,
two pork, how long, Roe?
ROE: Two pork,
seven minutes, please.
HEATHER: Seven minutes
to the window, Chef.
MIA: Thank you.
I'm one for one being
on winning brigades,
so I think this
bodes well for Mia.
Two pork in my hand.
Let's go to the promised land.
Pork, hot plate, Chef.
-How long--two sea bass?
-30 seconds.
Come on.
Roe!
Glazing right now, girl.
I'm glazing right now.
I need you up here right now.
She needs you to look
at that pork, Roe.
♪ ♪
The pork is raw, okay?
I need you to flash them.
Heard? How long?
-Two minutes.
HEATHER: Here come
the pork medallions back.
Roe, honey, they're thick.
You need to mark them
and get them in the oven
and let them finish.
If not, you're gonna sell
medium-rare pork again,
and I highly doubt
anybody wants that.
ROE: Heather, come here.
-Yeah, coming.
ROE: Can you check that?
If it's not good,
throw it back in.
GORDON: Why isn't he going?
What are we waiting on?
-We're waiting on pork.
-Oh, [bleep].
-How long, pork?
-Checking it now, Chef.
I don't want
to give you anything raw.
GORDON: Oh, man.
This ain't good.
What the [bleep] is going on?
-How long, pork?
J.B.: Uh-oh.
Roe?
Look around.
With artificial intelligence,
we are not crawling
or walking.
We are flying.
Microsoft AI helps an architect
bring history back to life.
This is now.
AI helps farmers grow more
food with less resources.
An engineer explores how
AI can help the Deaf
see sound.
Innovation creates tomorrow,
and tomorrow is here today.
♪ ♪
♪ Step it up. ♪
♪ Always take the risk. ♪
Don't just watch it...
Put your phone down and do it.
♪ Drip splash like the ice
on the wrist. ♪
♪ Brrt brrt brrt brrt ♪
♪ that's a call I can't miss. ♪
Let's do.
From the first loving touch
Pampers diapers are the #1
Choice of Hospitals,
and have been for over 40 years
Pampers Swaddlers
The #1 Choice of Hospitals,
Nurses & Parents
Not much here,
except the usual.
What if we spice
things up a bit?
Alexa...
"Fire"
by The Ohio Players
♪Fire (uh) (uh)♪
What if we turn it up a notch?
♪Fire (It's all about) (Uh, uh)♪
What if we go off the map?
♪Fire (Woo, woo, woo)♪
♪Fire♪
The all-new RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
[ music playing ]
♪ Here Comes the Sun ♪
You, all of you.
How you live. What you love.
[ laughter ]
That's what inspired us
to create America's
most advanced Internet.
Internet that
puts you in charge.
[ chattering ]
That protects what's important.
That handles everything
[ group cheering ]
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Xfinity.
The future of awesome.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
(dramatic music)
NARRATOR: It's 45 minutes into
the final dinner service...
Why isn't he going?
What are we waiting on?
MIA: We're waiting on pork.
-Oh, [bleep]
NARRATOR:
And rookie finalist Mia
has been left waiting on Roe
to deliver
properly cooked pork.
How long, pork?
ROE: One minute
on those refires, Mia.
MIA:
I won the challenge,
and Roe was my first pick
last night.
I thought
she was the strongest,
and this is
a little nerve-racking.
Super hot, super hot.
♪ ♪
-It's done.
-Go, go, go.
Amazing process to watch.
-Scary.
-Very scary.
Guys, listen up,
first entrées--
we're gonna go on
two rib cap, two wagyu.
-How long?
-I need eight minutes, Chef.
Eight minutes, two rib cap,
two wagyu heard.
I've never worked
with Scotley before,
so I'm gonna keep an eye
on him tonight,
and the menu's
a little lighter tonight,
so hopefully Scotley
can keep up.
-Oh, my God. Scotley.
-Right now, Chef.
-Scotley, watch your grill.
SCOTLEY: Heard.
We're charring on
our steaks over here.
SCOTLEY: Heard.
ARIEL: We want perfect
food tonight, okay?
It's not a race.
It always get annoying when,
you know,
you have a backseat driver.
Somebody over your shoulder
telling you how to cook.
Man, I got this.
I been doing this.
We got to watch the grill
because we're getting
too much char.
I would like to start
a couple new ones.
SCOTLEY: Yes, Chef.
ARIEL: Come on, man.
I'm not concerned
about rushing these out.
I want to make sure
we get them to the guests
the way they're intended
to be enjoyed.
All right, I need to see
those rib cap. Bring them up.
SCOTLEY: Bringing it
right now, Chef.
♪ ♪
That's perfectly cooked.
-Not more than this.
-Heard, Chef.
Trust me.
I'm here to help you.
ARIEL:
I need service, please.
Our chef seems
very self-assured.
-Yeah.
-All right, guys, next ticket.
You said three minutes.
You should be 30 seconds out.
Let's go.
Okay, so away now,
two chicken, two churrasco.
ALL: Heard.
HEATHER: Two chicken,
two beef, heard, Chef.
JOSE: Two chicken,
two churrasco.
MIA: Guys, I need five minutes
on that next check,
the two skirt
and the two chicken.
MIA: I'm a little nervous
about Heather.
She just lost to me,
so it may be a little difficult
to motivate her.
Nice sear, nice glaze,
medium-rare.
I just hope
that she can support me.
How long--two chicken,
two churrasco?
Give me three minutes on the
two beef and two chicken, yeah?
I'm all about carrying Mia
to victory,
whether we're BFFs or not.
Chicken and beef are up.
Let me know
when you're ready to walk.
You ready to go, Jose?
Let me go first,
yeah, two chicken.
I'm coming up.
Proteins walking.
Behind, Chef, hot.
Are they rested?
Yes, Chef.
Hopefully I lead Mia
into victory
'cause I know what it's like
to have my hand on that door
and it not open.
It hurts.
♪ ♪
-Heather, beautiful cook...
-Yes?
-On the protein.
-Thank you.
-Keep it coming, okay?
NARRATOR: With entrées
leaving Mia's kitchen
at a steady pace...
GORDON: Keep it going, Mia.
Keep it going.
-This is juicy and soft.
-Yeah.
NARRATOR: Over in the red
kitchen, veteran Ariel...
Guys, next ticket,
how long chicken, wagyu?
NARRATOR: Is continuing
to push Bret for perfection.
Walking as soon
as garnish is up, Chef.
ARIEL: Thank you.
Bret has a big responsibility.
He only has to cook
two proteins tonight,
so I need to make sure
that he nurses and babysits
that wagyu so that
it's absolutely perfect.
(fire crackling)
Oh, boy.
BRET: I wish I was
in the finale right now,
considering I was so close,
but Ariel--
she's a phenomenal chef,
and she deserves this win bad,
and I'm gonna do whatever I can
to [bleep] help her get it.
Chef, behind, chicken, wagyu.
He told me he walked up
chicken garnish
followed by steak garnish.
GORDON: [bleep] hell.
Really? It's cold.
We're serving
cold [bleep] food.
I need a little heat on this.
-Be very careful.
GORDON: Just touch it.
-I don't want it overcooked.
BRET: Heard, Chef.
I know it's a wagyu,
I get that,
-but it's barely lukewarm.
-Yes, Chef.
Timing's way off.
BRET: I feel bad whenever
I [bleep] up a food
or it's not 100% flawless
the first time
whether it's for Ariel,
Chef, any customer,
my clients, whatever.
I bring passion every time
I step in that kitchen.
BRET: Chef,
right behind to your left.
-ARIEL: Thank you.
-Get this on the plate.
It's got to send.
Service, please.
Let's go, let's go.
-Three pork, one churrasco.
-We got a minute and a half.
NARRATOR: After a few hiccups
from both teams...
Pick up two mackerel,
two wagyu, how long?
-Right now, Chef.
MOTTO: Right now.
NARRATOR:
The Hell's Kitchen rookie...
-Rested?
-Yes, Chef.
NARRATOR: And the
Hell's Kitchen veteran...
-Let's go. Send it up.
-Walking.
NARRATOR: Are now both
pushing out quality entrées
at a brisk pace...
GORDON: Got to go,
Got to go, got to go, got to go.
NARRATOR: And living up
to Chef Ramsay's
high expectations.
GORDON: Very good.
MIA: Perfect.
I'm not sharing this with you.
-This is too good.
MARSHA: Wow, that's great!
That is really good,
you know?
They did a good job.
Oh.
Away now--two sea bass,
two churrasco.
JOSE: Two sea bass--
-I want it perfect, Roe, okay?
ROE: Yes, ma'am.
-How long?
-Five minutes, five minutes.
-Five.
-You need five? That's fine.
-Yeah. Five.
Guys, this is
the last stretch, okay?
-Let's finish strong.
-Push it up.
'Cause I want you guys
to nail it.
We have
a really good pace going,
and it feels good, but I'm not
celebrating just yet.
Two sea bass,
two churrasco, how long?
You ready? I can go.
Do you need a minute?
ROE: I think I'm good.
HEATHER: Okay.
-Chef, coming in to the right.
-Yep.
♪ ♪
-How long on that sea bass?
-In my hand, Chef, walking.
♪ ♪
Is that the best
you can do, Roe?
It's falling apart.
GORDON: Were you boiling
it rapidly or steaming it?
-Steaming it, Chef.
-It looks terrible.
I always have
this problem that the minute
I go under on something,
I, like, overcompensate
on the next and go over.
Refire everything, guys--
garnish, protein, everything.
Heard.
For some unknown reason,
which I don't understand why,
Roe was the first pick
last night,
and I don't know if those
are big shoes to fill or what,
but she's dropping the ball.
How long for table four
to come out,
the main course,
more or less?
We're refiring it,
everything fresh.
-Okay. Perfect.
-So I'd rather be a bit slower
and perfect
than send something
that she's not happy with,
right?
-Okay, perfect.
-Piss off.
How long--two sea bass,
two churrasco?
Protein's walking.
-How long, sea bass?
TREV: Sea bass?
♪ ♪
It's okay?
ROE: For the love of God.
HEATHER:
You good, Roe?
-Are you happy with that?
MIA: Yes.
-Yes, I'm happy with that.
-Hallelujah.
-That's what I'm talking about.
Go.
Follow with the broth.
-This is the bass.
-Oh, my God.
All right, listen up,
I'm firing a six-top.
We're almost there, guys.
Keep pushing.
Two mackerel,
two chicken, two wagyu.
-Heard.
-Got it.
ARIEL: Guys, push for me, okay?
MOTTO: Yes, Chef.
Let's do it.
Let's finish strong.
Let's do it, yo.
Come on, yo.
-You guys are smashing this.
-Got you.
Service is going so great.
We're almost there.
We're down
to the last six-top.
-A-team, what, what?
TREV: What?
And let's finish as strong
as we started.
Where are we? Two mackerel,
two chicken, two wagyu?
TREV: How long on the mackerel?
SCOTLEY: 90 seconds.
I'll be there in 2 1/2
as long as garnish is ready.
This six-top
are the executives
from the Six Flags
Magic Mountain,
and I think they looked
after you last night, right?
ALL: Yes, Chef.
-Yes.
Let's go. I'm taking
your garnish on there.
Heard.
I'm bringing it right to you.
-Hot behind.
-Okay.
Look, hit me with some
vinegar here.
Come on, A-Team.
KANAE: A-Team.
♪ ♪
Hey, Scotley, that mackerel
is sexy, all right?
-Nice job.
-[smooches] For you, baby.
♪ ♪
Bret, can I get
a new chicken refire?
GORDON: How burnt is that skin?
-My fault, Chef. Sorry, Chef.
-The mackerel is cooked.
-Won't happen again, Chef.
Come on, Bret.
We're almost there.
Put your big-boy pants on,
and let's get
this [bleep] rolling.
-Bret, I need that chicken.
-30 seconds.
Let's go.
I don't want to give it
to you raw, Chef.
I [bleep] up with the chicken,
so I got to make sure
that this chicken's proper,
and, yabba dabba doo,
-we keep it moving.
-Bret, chicken?
MOTTO: Come on, Bret.
ARIEL: Let's go, Bret.
The mackerel's
been there two minutes.
BRET: Chicken, hot pan.
ARIEL: It's raw.
GORDON: [bleep]. Bret!
-Yes, Chef?
-Look at me!
-I would be freaking out.
-Wake up!
-I am awake, Chef!
Yeah, well, if you were awake,
you wouldn't be cooking
[bleep] raw chicken!
Wow.
Needles.
Essential for pine trees,
but maybe not for people
with rheumatoid arthritis.
Because there are options.
Like an "Unjection™".
XELJANZ XR.
A once-daily pill
for adults with moderate
to severe RA
for whom methotrexate
did not work well enough.
XELJANZ XR can reduce pain,
swelling
and further joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ XR can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes
fatal infections and cancers,
including lymphoma
have happened.
As have tears in the stomach
or intestines,
serious allergic reactions,
low blood cell counts,
higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels.
Don't start XELJANZ XR
if you have an infection.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before
and while taking XELJANZ XR,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you've been
somewhere fungal infections
are common and if you have had
TB, hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Needles.
Fine for some things.
But for you, one pill a day
may provide symptom relief.
Ask your doctor about
XELJANZ XR.
An "Unjection™".
♪♪
[Cell phone rings]
Where are you?
Well the squirrels
are back in the attic.
Mom?
Your dad won't
call an exterminator...
Can I call
you back, Mom?
He says it's
personal this time...
If you're a mom, you
call at the worst time.
It's what you do.
If you want to save fifteen
percent or more
on car insurance, you
switch to GEICO.
It's what you do.
Where are you?
It's very loud there.
Are you taking a
Zumba class?
Julie means more to
me than anything.
And I wanted to ask you
before I ask her.
May I have your permission,
to marry her?
You're not just marrying her.
You're marrying...
...her whole world.
Get zero-down special financing
on bridal purchases
with the Kay Jewelers
credit card.
♪♪
Here is another Laundry Hack
from Home Made Simple.
Do you want ready to wear
clothing without all the hassle?
You can, with Bounce Dryer
sheets.
Simply toss two sheets in the
dryer to iron less.
We dried one shirt without
Bounce,
and an identical shirt using
Bounce.
The Bounce shirt has fewer
wrinkles, less static,
and more softness and
freshness.
For extra large or wrinkly
loads, toss in three sheets.
Dermatologist tested Bounce Free
and Gentle
is free of dyes and perfumes.
Bounce out wrinkles, Bounce out
static.
(dramatic music)
Look at me!
-Wake up!
-I am awake, Chef!
Yeah, well, if you were awake,
you wouldn't be cooking
[bleep] raw chicken!
-Heard, Chef--
-Wake up a bit [bleep] more.
Enough's enough.
-Bret, come here, please.
-Still a little under?
That's why I didn't want
to serve it to you.
Yep, take that one.
Take that one.
Heard. Come on. If that one is,
then that one is.
Actually, both of them, yep.
Just give it two more minutes,
all right, Bret?
Heard, Chef.
We're so close
to the end of service.
We so don't have time
for these mistakes.
GORDON: Come on, Brett.
-I got it, Chef.
I'm finishing the steaks,
and I'm going.
Third [bleep] time.
We have to get
this food out right.
Very hot pan, very hot pan.
♪ ♪
Hey, Bret, your chicken
looks beautiful. Thank you.
-Thank you, Chef.
-Ariel, good job. Well done.
NARRATOR: With Bret finally
delivering perfect chicken...
-Last ticket of the night.
NARRATOR: Both Ariel and Mia
are pushing their brigades
toward the finish line.
MIA: Two chicken, two pork--
how long?
ROE: I need three minutes
in the oven.
JOSE: Two minutes.
-Nail it.
-Got it.
-Let's bring it home, guys.
Come on, guys, push it.
Guys, I need perfect food
on this table.
Let's go. Come on, y'all.
Finish strong for Ariel, man.
Two chicken, two pork--
how long?
I'm ready to go
in one minute, Chef.
-Pork, how long?
ROE: One minute for the pork.
-Taste it. I want it perfect.
GORDON: Keep it going. Good.
This is the last table.
Send it to me.
BRET: Ready to go.
Can I walk these steaks?
MOTTO: Yes, Chef.
I got two mackerel.
Chef, going in
to your right really hot.
ROE: Walking pork hot,
very hot, out of the oven.
MIA: Perfect.
Right behind, steaks going
with the two mackerel
right there--
thank you, Chef.
All right, mackerel's good.
Beautiful.
Hold on.
Go, go.
ARIEL: Service, please.
WOMAN: It is really good.
The temperature
is perfect.
-That's amazing, right?
-It melts in your mouth.
This is wonderful.
The detail in the presentation
really goes a long way.
Ladies,
how is everything?
-Oh, my God.
-Thank you.
-It's wonderful, love it.
Love the little general
in you.
Well, you have to be.
You have to be.
-You got to be a general.
-It gets busy, yes.
-A hustle is on point, baby.
-Thank you.
Have a great night.
Thank you very much.
You guys did a great job.
ARIEL:
I love you, too, man.
I am so glad service is over.
I hope Chef Ramsay
saw a true leader tonight,
a captain,
and someone that he can trust.
-Oh, you were so good.
-Thank you.
-It was so amazing.
Hey, I liked that mackerel.
It was pretty good.
You think you can fix that
for me some other time?
-(laughter)
-Huh?
Thank you, guys, so much.
Amazing work, everybody.
Amazing work. Thank you.
We had a few bumps, but
I'm happy and proud of myself.
I left all of it
in the kitchen.
Thank you so much.
I gave everything I had.
(smooches)
(exciting music)
♪ ♪
BRET:
I tried to do my best.
ARIEL:
You did a great job.
-You did a really nice job.
-Thank you.
I feel like it's gonna be a
very, very close call tonight.
I have no hard feelings
against Mia,
but I really hope that Ariel
wins today, seriously.
-Thank you for your work, Jose.
-You're very welcome.
-Thank you so much.
-Mia...
-I told you I got you.
I'm proud of Mia coming in
as a rookie
and proving
to the veterans that,
you know, we were stronger
than what they imagined.
Definitely feel like
Mia's taking this W home.
MIA:
Dinner service was great.
It's over now,
and this is when
the nerves really kick in,
'cause there's absolutely
nothing I can do anymore.
JOSE: Amazing job, both of you.
ARIEL: Thank you.
MIA: Thank you.
Thank you for your work.
BRET:
May the best lady win.
Congratulations
to the both of youse.
I'm proud of my team.
They did an amazing job.
I couldn't have asked
for a better team.
I'm just anxious now.
I can't sit down right now.
I'm wired right now,
[bleep] wired.
I feel relieved
because we got through
the final dinner service.
I think it went pretty well,
and I'm just moments away
from finding out
whether or not
I've won or not,
which is giving me
total anxiety.
TREV: Good job.
Good job.
I'm trying to just keep it
together for a minute.
-You'll be okay.
-I'm good.
♪ ♪
Would anybody like
some ice cream?
HEATHER: No, you're good.
(laughs)
I was like, "That's my dog."
GORDON:
Time to get serious.
-(knocks on door)
-(Heather gasps)
(Kanae gasps)
(gasping dramatically)
Chef Ramsay, what are
you doing here?
-We're doing karaoke later,
and you're gonna sing.
-Jamie, this is your house?
-I know, it's not much,
but it's home.
Right, kids?
-Kids?
-Papa, Papa!
-[ Laughs ]
-You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
-Oh, yeah.
-This one is tiny like a child.
-Yeah, she is.
Oh, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most --
a home and auto bundle
from Progressive.
-Oh, sweetie,
please, play for us.
-Oh, no, I couldn't.
-Please.
-Okay.
[ Singing in Spanish ]
I've hunted every dragon.
-Please.
-Okay.
This is full blown war.
We'll never give them up.
How To Train Your Dragon
the Hidden World
THIS IS A TEST.
FL
[ growl ]
Cute.
Ahh!
Now that's a king.
Right now, you can get two
KFC Chicken Littles for 3 bucks.
It doesn't get any
better then that.
"Frying sound"
"Kapushh"
"Shooo Shoop"
"Shoop"
"Kapah!"
Actually, with four
flavors to choose from,
it did get better,
and I stand corrected.
Get any 2 KFC Chicken
Littles for 3 dollars.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
♪ All the ways, all the ways ♪
♪ Tell me all the ways  ♪
♪ And he said ♪
♪ Girl, you take care of me ♪
♪ You are my therapy ♪
♪ The better half of me ♪
♪ Say it again ♪
♪ If you love me,
love me, love me ♪
♪ Like you say ♪
♪ Darling tell me all the ways ♪
♪ Tell me all the ways ♪
Now, we're bringing
you all the ways
to get what you need.
Target Run & Done.
Your favorite restaurants now
deliver with DoorDash.
♪
It doesn't matter
where you are.
♪
It doesn't matter what
you're hungry for.
It doesn't even matter
how many you are.
♪
Restaurants come to you.
Delicious at your door.
Download DoorDash.
First order, no delivery fee.
(dramatic music)
GORDON:
Time to get serious.
-(knock on door)
-(Heather gasps)
-(Kanae gasps)
-So this is where you live?
-Nice.
KANAE: Look, behind you.
GORDON:
Oh, my God.
You got to look at this
all the time?
BRET: Hell, yeah.
HEATHER: Yeah.
I'm not one for apologizing,
but I am sorry about
that [bleep] mess on there.
-(laughter)
JOSE: No, Chef.
First of all,
let me tell our returning chefs
how much I appreciate
the effort
that you all put in
across tonight's service.
Not only did you
support your chefs,
but you guys
had a good service.
ALL:
Thank you, Chef.
ROE: Even after, you know,
being eliminated,
I will bleed for Chef Ramsay.
That's the hierarchy.
That's your mentor.
We got a lot
more things to do,
and I am miles away
from being ready,
but for now,
I'd like both of you to say
good-bye to your brigades...
ALL: Bye, guys.
GORDON: And your sous chefs.
-See you in a little bit?
-Yep.
ARIEL: Thank you.
MIA: Thank you so much
for tonight.
Guys, head
into the dining room.
I'll see you there shortly.
BRET:
Hell, yeah, let's do it.
♪ ♪
GORDON:
Scallops are cooked beautifully.
I love what you did
with the celery root.
You've done something
pretty magical.
-Thank you, Chef.
-Good job.
GORDON:
Just look at that--textbook.
-Thank you, Chef.
-The first recipient
of the black jacket,
congratulations, Ariel.
-Thank you, Chef.
-Great job.
Thank you.
Why do I have tuna? I need two
beef tartare, not tuna tartare.
Look at me. Well spotted.
♪ ♪
It's amazing.
GORDON: I want to get
to the end, and I want more.
-Yes.
MOTTO: Awesome.
You did a really nice job
on the steaming on this fish.
I'll take the rest to go.
This is a delicious dish.
It is worthy of being on a menu
right now in a restaurant.
-Peanut butter.
-Yes!
-Good girl.
-Nice work, Mia.
-Four for four.
-It doesn't look like lobster.
You're absolutely right,
well spotted.
-It is monkfish.
-Yes, Chef.
♪ ♪
MIA: This is it, girl.
ARIEL: (laughing) I know.
This is bananas.
I'm having, like,
an out-of-body experience
right now.
Yeah.
I said in the beginning
I thought Mia
was my biggest competition,
and I think that she overcame
a lot of hurdles,
but I think based
on my performance
that I won "Hell's Kitchen."
Let's get this over with.
I'm gonna beat Ariel
because I feel like
we're at the same level
as far as leadership goes.
I feel like my dishes
are more creative.
So I definitely think
I'm the next executive chef
at the flagship Hell's Kitchen
restaurant in Las Vegas.
-(phone ringing)
-Scared me.
(laughs)
Hi, this is Mia.
GORDON: Hi, Mia.
I've made my decision.
Can you and Ariel please make
your way to my office?
-Yes, Chef.
-Thank you.
He said make our way
to his office.
♪ ♪
MIA: This is it, girl.
(cheers and applause)
MAN: Let's go, Mia!
Let's go, Mia!
(cheers and applause continue)
Right, you two, welcome.
Ariel, Mia, this has been an
extremely difficult decision,
let me tell you.
Mia, never before
have we had a chef
that has performed so strongly
across challenges.
Above that, you've been one
of the most creative chefs
we've ever had
in Hell's Kitchen.
-Thank you, Chef.
-Ariel...
-Yes, Chef?
-You have been
the most consistent chef
across this
entire competition,
so it's no surprise to me
that you are the only chef
on either team
never to be considered
for elimination.
Ariel, right now
how are you feeling?
Ugh, my stomach is in knots,
Chef, to be honest with you.
I'm just trying
to contain myself
and maintain my calm
that I've had all season.
Mia, what's going
through your mind?
My heart is racing,
but I'm just so proud
of what I've accomplished,
and I'm really proud of myself,
and I'm so grateful for all
the faith you've had in me.
I could not be prouder
of the two of you.
In my eyes,
you're both winners.
BOTH:
Thank you, Chef.
Mia and Ariel,
please step up
in front of your doors.
BOTH: Yes, Chef.
♪ ♪
MIA: For me,
everything is on the line.
This is what I want.
I've been
completely sure of myself.
I came to this competition
to get here.
This is it.
ARIEL:
This is a huge opportunity.
This is the perfect
next place for me to be.
It just feels so right
that if it doesn't happen,
I'm just gonna be so confused
and just so bummed out.
The chef whose door opens
will become the winner
of "Hell's Kitchen"
and the executive chef
of the flagship
Hell's Kitchen restaurant
at Caesars Palace Las Vegas,
with a salary
of $1/4 million dollars.
♪ ♪
Both of you very carefully
place your hand
on top of your door handle.
♪ ♪
On the count of three,
I want you
to turn your handles.
♪ ♪
One, two...
Three.
(cheers and applause)
Ahhh...
Boommm!
Wow!
Lemme ask you a question,
who is the play-maker of this
new Big Mac with Bacon?
It's the crispy
bacon, of course.
The flavor brings a whole
new dimension to the game.
Bacon does not
win championships.
Special Sauce wins
championships, my friend!
You're wrong.
And I'm a doctor.
Which means I'm
always right.
I'm gonna get a second
opinion, from my mouth.
McDonald's Classics with
Bacon, only for a limited time.
Is it the best thing to
happen to our Classics?
Or to bacon?
Try r yourself
and decide.
This Valentine's Day,
give her your heart.
Or, ask her for her hand.
Save 25% off everything.
Plus, enjoy specials
like these diamond earrings
for just $59.
Only through February 11th.
At Zales. The Diamond Store.
♪ ♪
♪ Step it up. ♪
♪ Always take the risk. ♪
Don't just watch it...
Put your phone down and do it.
♪ Drip splash like the ice
on the wrist. ♪
♪ Brrt brrt brrt brrt ♪
♪ that's a call I can't miss. ♪
Let's do.
Sweat.
Dedication.
Cupcakes.
I'm Michael Griffin.
I'm Brian Orakpo.
We played football together for
the Titans.
Now, we own a cupcake shop.
We bake, we decorate.
I love this new Surface Pro.
It's light, it's sleek, it's
fast.
I'm able to draw what color
frosting we want.
We do a lot with social media.
We have funny videos that we do
in the bakery [laughs].
There's nothing that you can't
do on this device.
Cupcakes are a great business.
Oh yeah, as long as you don't
eat the profits!
(dramatic music)
The chef whose door opens
will become the executive chef
of the flagship
Hell's Kitchen restaurant
at Caesars Palace Las Vegas,
with a salary
of $1/4 million dollars.
Good luck.
On the count of three, I want
you to turn your handles.
One, two...
♪ ♪
Three.
(cheers and applause)
MAN: [bleep], yeah!
(cheers and applause continue)
Yes! Yes! Yes!
♪ ♪
Mia...
Thank you, Chef.
That was amazing.
Well done.
Thank you, Chef.
You're gonna have
a phenomenal career.
-Thank you so much, Chef.
-No doubt, okay?
Thank you for the opportunity.
I'm so proud to have gotten
to this place as a rookie.
You know, I knocked out
everybody but one,
and this isn't the end for me.
Like, this is
just the beginning.
-(cheers and applause)
-MAN: Yeah!
I have been to Hell's Kitchen
twice and made it out alive,
and not only alive,
but I made it out a winner,
and this feels incredible
right now.
(cheers and applause continue)
Um... (laughs)
-Great job.
-Thank you.
Come on.
Go down those stairs.
They'd like to see you.
Come on.
(cheers and applause continue)
Let's go.
MAN:
A-team! A-team! A-team!
Oh, [bleep]!
This job is made for me.
I am the person who says every
single day when I go to bed,
"How am I gonna be better
than I was yesterday?"
(sobbing)
Thank you.
ARIEL: I dedicate winning
to both my parents.
I'm happy to show my parents
how far I've come.
Every time they see me succeed,
it makes them feel happy.
Mia, I have so much
respect for you.
I think that you
are so talented,
and when I go to Las Vegas,
if you want to come,
if I have the position
for you, it's yours.
I would hire you
in a heartbeat.
Would you like to hear from
the "Hell's Kitchen" winner?
ALL: Yes!
Come on.
I am so [bleep]
excited right now.
(laughs) I'm sorry.
I am so excited to work
with this incredible woman
right here, Chef Christina.
I can't wait to work for you.
I can't wait to work with you,
Chef Jocky,
and of course, Chef,
I am very excited to show you
-what I have in store, so...
-Cannot wait.
Thank you
for this opportunity.
Incredible,
amazing, thank you.
Wow.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our "Hell's Kitchen"
winner, Ariel!
(cheers and applause)
GORDON: Since the first time
she was here,
Ariel has grown tenfold
as a chef.
She is fiercely talented,
extremely determined,
and a commanding leader.
I could not be more pleased
to have her
as my executive chef
of Hell's Kitchen in Las Vegas.
One final thing to do--
it's a tradition here
in Hell's Kitchen.
Hang that up.
-We got it?
-Get it on there?
I don't know.
It's up to you.
Come on, carpenter,
straighten that out.
(laughs)
-Yay.
-Well done.
ARIEL:
To feel like you did well
and to know
that you earned something
and that you belong there
is an amazing feeling.
WOMAN: A-team!
This has been the most
rewarding journey
of my entire life.
I have worked so hard
in my career,
and to just be
so validated right now
for everything
that I have ever done
is the most satisfying feeling
I have ever felt.
-Cheers!
-Yeah, one big clink, cheers.
MAN: Cheers!
Hell's Kitchen.
-Cheers.
-Whoo! Season 18.
Season 18.
Announcer:  Wednesday, Gordon
heads to Hollyood to save a
struggling restaurant on a new
24 Hours to Hell and Back.
>>> RIGHT NOW AT 10:00.
A SECOND WOMAN IS ACCUSING
VIRGINIA'S LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR
OF RAPE.
THIS, AS THE GOVERNOR DOUBLED
THIS, AS THEElyse:NOR DOUBLED
WE'RE THE HISTORY DETECTIVES,
AND WE'RE GOING TO INVESTIGATE
SOME UNTOLD STORIES
FROM AMERICA'S PAST.
Gwendolyn:
THIS WEEK...
She has already been taken
into custody by the FBI.
WHAT EVIDENCE FROM
THE TREASON TRIAL OF TOKYO ROSE
COULD THIS ODD DISC HOLD?
IT BECAME A COVER-UP.
Elyse:
IS THIS THE HOLY GRAIL
OF THE WILD WEST?
A PHOTOGRAPH OF THE LEGENDARY
WARRIOR CRAZY HORSE.
NOBODY HAS EVER PRODUCED A
PHOTOGRAPH OF CRAZY HORSE, EVER.
Wes:
AND IN AN ENCORE PRESENTATION,
DOES THIS DIARY HOLD THE KEY
TO UNDERSTANDING THE FATE
OF A MISSING BOMBER PILOT
FROM WORLD WAR II?
Elvis Costello:
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ I GET SO ANGRY
WHEN THE TEARDROPS START ♪
♪ BUT HE CAN'T BE WOUNDED
'CAUSE HE'S GOT NO HEART ♪
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ IT'S JUST LIKE
WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
Gwendolyn:
THIS PROGRAM WAS MADE POSSIBLE
BY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO YOUR PBS STATION
FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.
OUR FIRST STORY EXPLORES
WHETHER THIS 1940s RECORDING
MAY HAVE HELPED CONVICT
THE WOMAN ALLEGED TO BE
TOKYO ROSE.
WORLD WAR II,
THE LONELY PACIFIC:
AS MANY AS 2 MILLION SERVICEMEN
LISTEN WISTFULLY
WHILE A WOMAN'S VOICE
FLOATS OVER THE AIRWAVES.
Greetings, everybody.
This is your number-one enemy,
your favorite playmate...
THEY CALL HER
TOKYO ROSE.
MANY G.I.s CONSIDERED HER
A GODSEND,
A FAMILIAR AMERICAN VOICE
KEEPING THEM COMPANY
FAR FROM HOME.
BUT IN A CELEBRATED
POSTWAR TRIAL,
PROSECUTORS PORTRAYED HER
AS AN AMERICAN DEVIL,
A SIREN WHO KNOWINGLY WORKED
FOR THE ENEMY,
LURING SOLDIERS AND SAILORS,
THEN UNDERMINING
THEIR FIGHTING SPIRIT.
IN 1948, THE WOMAN
WHO TWICE SIGNED HER NAME
"THE ONE AND ORIGINAL
TOKYO ROSE"
WAS BROUGHT BACK FROM JAPAN
TO FACE A GRAND JURY.
THE WAR HAD ENDED,
BUT HER BATTLE HAD JUST BEGUN.
NOW BILL MOORE
FROM SUN CITY WEST, ARIZONA,
HAS AN OBJECT THAT MAY EXPLAIN
THE STORY BEHIND
HER CONFESSION.
MY UNCLE WENT TO JAPAN
TO GET TOKYO ROSE.
HI, YOU'RE BILL?
SO I HEAR YOU HAVE
A RECORD TO SHOW ME.
IS THIS IT?
YES, THIS IS IT.
WOW, IT'S UNUSUAL.
THIS MUST BE 16 INCHES ACROSS.
SIXTEEN INCHES, I THINK.
SOMEONE'S WRITTEN "TOKYO ROSE"
ON THE RECORD.
BILL FOUND IT WITH HIS MOTHER'S
THINGS AFTER SHE PASSED AWAY,
BUT HE BELIEVES
IT ORIGINALLY BELONGED
TO HIS LARGER-THAN-LIFE UNCLE,
HARRY BRUNDIDGE.
THIS IS MY UNCLE HARRY
AND MY AUNT JANET.
WHAT DID HE DO?
WELL, HE WAS
A WAR CORRESPONDENT
AND ASSOCIATE EDITOR
OF COSMOPOLITAN MAGAZINE.
THIS IS YOU, IS THAT RIGHT?
OH, YEAH.
SO WERE YOU OUT
IN THE PACIFIC?
TWO YEARS,
AND WE USED TO LISTEN
TO TOKYO ROSE ALL THE TIME.
BILL HAD HEARD THAT HIS UNCLE
MET TOKYO ROSE ON ASSIGNMENT
AND BELIEVES HE PLAYED
A KEY ROLE IN HER PROSECUTION.
AFTER THE WAR,
HE WENT BACK OVER TO JAPAN
AND HE GOT TOKYO ROSE,
BROUGHT HER BACK
TO SAN FRANCISCO,
AND HAD HER INDICTED
FOR TREASON.
BILL THINKS THE RECORD
MAY HAVE BEEN USED
AS EVIDENCE
IN HER TRIAL,
BUT HE'S NEVER BEEN ABLE
TO HEAR WHAT'S ON THE RECORDING
BECAUSE IT'S TOO LARGE
TO PLAY ON STANDARD EQUIPMENT.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT -- OF COURSE,
WHAT I HEARD FROM MY FAMILY,
THAT THIS WAS
PART OF THE TRIAL.
WHAT EXACTLY WOULD YOU LIKE
FOR ME TO FIND OUT
ABOUT YOUR RECORD?
I'D LIKE TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S ON IT, OF COURSE,
AND ABOUT MY UNCLE
IN THE TRIAL.
I'LL HAVE TO TAKE THIS
WITH ME, AND I'D LIKE TO TAKE
THE PHOTOGRAPHS, TOO,
IF THAT'S OKAY.
OH, YOU CAN, YEAH.
I FOUND A STUDIO
WITH A TURNTABLE
THAT CAN PLAY
THE OVERSIZED DISC.
I'M IN LONG ISLAND CITY,
NEW YORK,
TO MEET AUDIO ENGINEER
GUY ROSMARIN AT VIDIPAX.
OOH, WOW, I HAVEN'T SEEN
ONE OF THESE IN A WHILE.
WHAT IS IT MADE OF?
PROBABLY ALUMINUM-BASED.
THEY STARTED USING IT AGAIN
AFTER THE WAR.
YOU COULDN'T USE ALUMINUM
DURING THE WAR
FOR ANYTHING EXCEPT WAR.
THAT'S RIGHT.
Female Voice:
All right, take it now
from five.
Tokyo Rose will touch
American soil in a few moments
and will immediately be taken
into custody.
WELL, THIS CERTAINLY DOESN'T
SOUND LIKE COURTROOM EVIDENCE,
BUT BILL'S UNCLE IS DEFINITELY
PART OF THE ACTION.
We're fortunate today in having
two very famous correspondents.
Harry Brundidge...
GUY HAS MADE A CD COPY FOR ME.
BILL'S UNCLE HARRY
IS SPEAKING NOW.
She just shook hands with me
as she came off the boat
and recognized me.
Female Voice:
I noticed that.
IVA TOGURI, THE WOMAN
WHO WAS TRIED AS TOKYO ROSE,
WAS BORN IN LOS ANGELES
TO FIRST-GENERATION
JAPANESE IMMIGRANTS.
SHE LEFT THE U.S.
IN THE SUMMER OF '41
TO CARE FOR A SICK AUNT
IN TOKYO.
AFTER PEARL HARBOR,
WARTIME BUREAUCRACY
MADE IT IMPOSSIBLE FOR HER
TO RETURN TO THE U.S.
STRANDED IN JAPAN
DURING THE WAR,
IVA FOUND A JOB
AT RADIO TOKYO AS A TYPIST
UNTIL SHE WAS TAPPED
TO HOST
A JAPANESE WAR
PROPAGANDA PROGRAM.
IVA'S BROADCASTS WOULD BE
AT THE CENTER OF WHAT WAS THEN
ONE OF THE COSTLIEST TRIALS
IN U.S. HISTORY.
THAT TRIAL COST
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT $750,000.
IN TODAY'S MONEY
THAT'S ALMOST $7 MILLION.
OF THE EIGHT COUNTS
BROUGHT AGAINST HER,
THE GRAND JURY FOUND HER GUILTY
OF ONLY ONE,
ANNOUNCING THE LOSS
OF AMERICAN SHIPS.
I'M IN NEW YORK CITY,
MEETING WITH MEDIA HISTORIAN
STEVEN PHIPPS.
I'M EAGER FOR YOU
TO HEAR THIS.
Female Voice:
There are crowds here
that have been standing
since 9:00 this morning
waiting to see Tokyo Rose,
the girl who undermined
the morale -- or tried to --
of our boys
in the Pacific.
WELL, THIS IS OBVIOUSLY
A NEWS REPORT,
AND IT'S CLEAR THAT IT MUST
HAVE BEEN SEPTEMBER 25, 1948.
STEVEN SAYS THAT'S WHEN IVA
RETURNED TO THE UNITED STATES
BY MILITARY ESCORT.
THE PRESS AND PUBLIC CLAMORED
FOR A CLOSER LOOK
AT THE WOMAN THE MEDIA
HAD ALREADY BRANDED
A WARTIME TRAITOR:
TOKYO ROSE.
BUT THERE WAS NO EVIDENCE
THAT SHE WAS THE TOKYO ROSE.
IN FACT, THERE WAS NO ONE PERSON
WHO WAS THE TOKYO ROSE.
AS BILL TOLD ME EARLIER,
THE G.I.s USED THAT NAME
FOR ALL THE ENGLISH-SPEAKING
FEMALE HOSTS
BROADCASTING IN THE PACIFIC.
THE JAPANESE FELT THAT
USING A WOMAN ANNOUNCER
WOULD MAKE THE G.I.s
MORE PRONE TO LISTEN
AND THAT IT WOULD TEND
TO MAKE THEM HOMESICK.
WHY DID BRUNDIDGE CLAIM
IVA WAS TOKYO ROSE?
STEVEN HAS DONE SOME DIGGING
ON THE REPORTER'S BACKGROUND.
I FOUND QUITE A FEW ARTICLES
ON BRUNDIDGE,
SINCE I KNOW THAT
YOU'RE INTERESTED IN HIM.
MUCH OF HIS EARLY CAREER
WAS IN ST. LOUIS,
REPORTING ON THE MOB.
STEVEN DISCOVERED BRUNDIDGE
HAD A FLAIR FOR THE DRAMATIC
AND OFTEN PLAYED FAST AND LOOSE
WITH THE FACTS.
HERE'S ONE FROM 1930.
THIS ONE IS CALLED
"CALL BRUNDIDGE STORY HEARSAY."
SO FOR YEARS HE'D
BEEN KNOWN AS SOMEONE
WHO WAS PUSHING
THE TRUTH ON HIS STORIES.
WELL, YES.
WHAT WAS HIS INVOLVEMENT
IN THE TOKYO ROSE STORY?
LET ME SHOW YOU
IN THIS ARTICLE.
IT'S A MAY 1948
FRONT-PAGE STORY
FROM THE NASHVILLE TENNESSEAN.
THAT'S FOUR MONTHS BEFORE
THE DATE ON OUR RECORDING.
IN IT, BRUNDIDGE DETAILS
HIS TIME IN JAPAN
HUNTING FOR EMPEROR HIROHITO,
THEN FOR TOKYO ROSE.
IN HIS STORY, BRUNDIDGE TAKES
CREDIT FOR HER INDICTMENT.
THERE'S A REFERENCE
TO SECRET WITNESSES
THAT BRUNDIDGE CAME UP WITH.
BUT DO WE KNOW
WHO THEY WERE?
I HAVE NO CLUE.
STEVEN GIVES ME THE NAME
OF A JOURNALIST
WHO REVISITED THIS STORY
IN THE 1970s.
RON YATES,
ONCE THE TOKYO BUREAU CHIEF
OF THE CHICAGO TRIBUNE,
WROTE A SERIES OF ARTICLES
IN 1976
ON THE TOKYO ROSE TRIAL.
WE'VE AGREED TO MEET
AT THE JAPANESE AMERICAN
NATIONAL MUSEUM IN LOS ANGELES.
WELL, HERE'S THE RECORD
I WAS TELLING YOU ABOUT, RON.
OH, WOW, LOOK AT THAT.
I'M INVESTIGATING A MAN
NAMED HARRY BRUNDIDGE.
THEY MENTION HIM
ON THIS RECORDING.
DO YOU KNOW WHO HE WAS?
OH, YEAH, HARRY BRUNDIDGE IS
A VERY INTERESTING CHARACTER.
RON EXPLAINS
HOW HARRY BRUNDIDGE
HAD FIRST BECOME INVOLVED
WITH TOKYO ROSE
THREE YEARS BEFORE THE TRIAL
IN THE IMMEDIATE AFTERMATH
OF WORLD WAR II.
THAT'S WHEN BRUNDIDGE
HOOKED UP WITH
VETERAN WAR CORRESPONDENT
CLARK LEE.
THEY HEADED TO JAPAN
IN 1945
IN PURSUIT OF THE SCOOP
OF A LIFETIME.
THEY THOUGHT, "WE'LL FIND TOKYO
ROSE AND THAT'LL BE OUR STORY."
THEY SAID, "WE WILL PAY HER
$2,000 IF SHE'LL COME
TO THE IMPERIAL HOTEL
TO BE INTERVIEWED."
IN WAR-TORN TOKYO, WHERE
MOST PEOPLE WERE STARVING,
THAT MONEY MIGHT GET HER HOME
TO THE UNITED STATES.
BUT WHEN SHE WALKED
INTO THE ROOM,
THIS WAS NOT
WHAT THEY WERE EXPECTING.
IN HER PIGTAILS
AND SADDLE SHOES,
IVA NEITHER LOOKED
NOR SOUNDED THE PART
OF THE MATAHARI OF THE EAST.
RON SHOWS ME A REENACTMENT
OF A ZERO HOUR BROADCAST
THAT IVA LATER AGREED TO DO
FOR THE U.S. ARMY IN TOKYO.
Greetings, everybody.
This is your number-one enemy,
your favorite playmate,
Orphan Ann, ready again
for a vicious assault
on your morale.
RON EXPLAINS THAT
ALL THE SCRIPTS
WERE WRITTEN
BY ALLIED P.O.W.s,
WHO ALSO HAD BEEN FORCED
TO WORK FOR RADIO TOKYO.
THE LANGUAGE WAS INTENDED
TO BE TONGUE-IN-CHEEK,
THE KIND OF TEASING
THAT AMERICANS
WOULD EASILY RECOGNIZE.
AND THEY'D ALWAYS GO OVER
THE SCRIPTS WITH HER AND SAY,
"HERE'S WHAT WE WANT YOU
TO SAY, IVA."
AND THEN SHE WOULD SAY
THESE THINGS,
LIKE "HELLO, MY HONORABLE
BONEHEADS OF THE PACIFIC.
"THIS IS YOUR FAVORITE ENEMY,
ORPHAN ANN.
I'M GOING TO SNEAK UP BEHIND YOU
WITH MY NAIL FILE."
YOU SEE IN HER FACE THAT
SHE KNOWS SHE'S SAYING THINGS
THAT WOULD SOUND MEAN
TO THE JAPANESE
BUT THAT IT'S ACTUALLY AN INSIDE
JOKE AMONG ALL THE AMERICANS.
RIGHT, THERE'S A REAL
FACETIOUSNESS TO IT.
WHEN BRUNDIDGE AND LEE
INTERVIEWED IVA IN 1945,
THAT TEASING TONE NEVER MADE IT
INTO THEIR NOTES.
THEY HAD OTHER PLANS.
THE STORY JUST WASN'T THERE.
THIS WAS NOT THE SIREN
OF THE PACIFIC.
BRUNDIDGE TOOK OUT THE CONTRACT
FOR $2,000,
THEN ASKED IVA
A FATEFUL QUESTION.
"JUST FOR THE HECK OF IT,
WOULD YOU JUST SIGN THIS
AS TOKYO ROSE?"
AND SHE SAID, "SURE."
WHAT HE DID WAS
HE TOOK THOSE NOTES
AND GAVE THEM TO THE
OCCUPATION FORCES, AUTHORITIES,
AND SAID, "I HAVE THE SIGNED
CONFESSION OF TOKYO ROSE HERE."
AND WITHIN A FEW DAYS
SHE WAS ARRESTED.
SHE WAS FIRST IMPRISONED
IN TOKYO UNDER MARTIAL LAW
AND HELD FOR A YEAR
WHILE THE ARMY
COUNTER INTELLIGENCE CORPS
INVESTIGATED.
FINDING NO EVIDENCE
OF TREASON,
THE WAR DEPARTMENT CLEARED
AND FINALLY RELEASED HER.
THAT SHOULD HAVE BEEN
THE END OF IT.
SO BRUNDIDGE MET HER IN '45,
'46 SHE'S RELEASED FROM PRISON,
HOW DID IT BECOME A STORY
AGAIN IN 1948?
THAT IS A STORY IN ITSELF.
AFTER BEING FREED
BY THE U.S. ARMY,
IVA HAD APPLIED
FOR REPATRIATION.
BUT THE POPULAR RADIO HOST
WALTER WINCHELL
LEARNED OF THE REQUEST
AND STARTED A CAMPAIGN
TO PREVENT HER RETURN
AND TRY HER FOR TREASON.
GOLD STAR MOTHERS --
THESE ARE MOTHERS
WHO HAD LOST THEIR SONS
FIGHTING IN THE PACIFIC --
BEGAN WRITING
TO WALTER WINCHELL,
HE FORWARDED THOSE
TO THE TRUMAN ADMINISTRATION,
AND THAT PRESSURE BEGAN
TO BUILD.
IT WAS AN ELECTION YEAR.
RON SAYS CHARGES OF BEING SOFT
ON COMMUNISTS AND TRAITORS
WAS A CRITICAL FACTOR
IN TRUMAN'S CLOSE PRESIDENTIAL
RACE AGAINST THOMAS DEWEY.
THE TRUMAN ADMINISTRATION
DOESN'T WANT TO BE PERCEIVED
AS BEING SOFT ON TRAITORS.
THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE
ISSUED A REQUEST FOR WITNESSES
TO IVA'S ALLEGED ACTS
OF TREASON.
SO HERE COMES BRUNDIDGE AGAIN.
WHEN BRUNDIDGE MET UP WITH
ATTORNEY GENERAL TOM CLARK,
HE OFFERED TO GET
A NEW CONFESSION FROM IVA
AND TO FIND WITNESSES
TO HELP CONVICT HER.
TOM CLARK ASSIGNS SOME OF
HIS MINIONS TO GO BACK TO TOKYO,
AND HARRY BRUNDIDGE
GOES WITH THEM.
RON SAYS IT WASN'T UNTIL
A QUARTER-CENTURY
AFTER IVA'S TRIAL
THAT HE UNLOCKED
A CRUCIAL PIECE
OF THE GOVERNMENT'S STRATEGY.
RON ARRANGED TO MEET TWO MEN
WHO HAD HELD ON TO A SECRET:
GEORGE MITSUSHIO
AND KEN OKI,
IVA'S OLD BOSSES
FROM RADIO TOKYO.
THEY SAID, "WE -- OUR TESTIMONY
IS WHAT CONVICTED HER,
AND IT WAS ALL A LIE."
THEY HAD BEEN COACHED
FOR TWO MONTHS
BY THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
IN WHAT THEY SHOULD SAY
AT THE TRIAL.
AND THEIR TESTIMONY WAS
THE SIXTH OF THE EIGHT COUNTS
WHICH SHE WAS INDICTED ON,
THAT SHE DID SPEAK
INTO A MICROPHONE
ABOUT THE LOSS OF SHIPS.
BUT WHAT ABOUT
BRUNDIDGE'S CLAIMS
OF FINDING ADDITIONAL
SECRET WITNESSES?
I KNOW THE PERFECT PERSON
TO TELL YOU ABOUT THEM.
I'M MEETING WITH BARBARA
TREMBLEY AT DARKWOOD STUDIOS.
BARBARA MET IVA
20 YEARS AGO.
OVER TIME THEY BECAME FRIENDS.
IVA AGREED TO TELL
HER FULL STORY
AND GAVE BARBARA THE RIGHTS
TO MAKE HER SAGA
INTO A FEATURE FILM.
I HAVE A RECORDING
THAT IS DESCRIBING THE MOMENT
WHEN IVA COMES BACK
TO THE UNITED STATES.
I TELL BARBARA THAT
ON THIS RECORDING
BRUNDIDGE BOASTS OF GETTING IVA
TO SIGN A NEW CONFESSION.
WHY IS IVA EVEN WILLING
TO SEE HIM,
MUCH LESS TO SIGN
THIS DOCUMENT?
SHE HAD JUST LOST HER BABY.
BARBARA EXPLAINS THAT IVA
HAD JUST SUFFERED A MISCARRIAGE
AND DESPERATELY WANTED
TO GET HOME TO THE STATES.
IVA TOLD BARBARA THAT
BRUNDIDGE HAD ASSURED HER
THAT SIGNING THE DOCUMENT
WAS A PASSPORT HOME.
AND THEN AS SOON
AS SHE SIGNED IT,
BRUNDIDGE LEANED OVER TO IVA
AND HE SAID,
"YOU'VE DONE YOURSELF
A GOOD DEAL.
THEY'LL NEVER EXECUTE
A WOMAN."
SHE LOST HER HEART
AT THAT POINT.
BRUNDIDGE HAD WRITTEN
ABOUT SECRET WITNESSES
THAT WOULD PROVE THE CASE
AGAINST IVA.
YES, MR. YAGI.
YAGI WAS ACTUALLY SOMEONE
THAT BRUNDIDGE HAD KNOWN
BEFORE THE WAR.
BARBARA SAYS THAT WHEN
BRUNDIDGE TRAVELED TO JAPAN,
HIROM YAGI ACTED AS A FIXER,
MAKING LOCAL INTRODUCTIONS
FOR THE JOURNALIST.
BRUNDIDGE LITERALLY BRIBED HIM.
HE SAID, "YOU WILL GET
A TRIP TO THE U.S.
"AND WE'LL HAVE
A WONDERFUL TIME.
"ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS TESTIFY
FOR THE GRAND JURY,
AND THIS IS ALL
YOU HAVE TO SAY."
BARBARA FOUND
THE HANDWRITTEN TESTIMONY
YAGI HAD GIVEN BRUNDIDGE
AND THE U.S. ATTORNEY GENERAL.
"I HEARD HER SAY
INTO THE MICROPHONE,
'YOUR WIVES ARE OUT
WITH WAR WORKERS.'"
SO DOES HE TESTIFY
AT THE TRIAL
BEFORE THE GRAND JURY?
YES, HE DOES.
BUT AS SOON AS HE GETS BACK
TO JAPAN, HE RECANTS.
YAGI EVEN WRITES A LETTER
TO BRUNDIDGE
ASKING HIM TO PLEASE STOP THIS
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
"DEAR MR. BRUNDIDGE, THIS IS
AN ELEVENTH HOUR APPEAL
"ASKING YOU TO USE
YOUR GOOD INFLUENCES
TO CALL OFF THE COMING TRIAL,
IF POSSIBLE."
BARBARA EXPLAINS THAT BY NOW
THE GOVERNMENT
HAD SERIOUS DOUBTS
ABOUT BRUNDIDGE
AND EVEN BEGAN TO INVESTIGATE
HIM FOR WITNESS TAMPERING,
BUT THEY HAD TOO MUCH INVESTED
IN THE TRIAL TO BACK OUT NOW.
THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE,
TOM CLARK, AND SO ON,
THEY PUT A LID ON IT
AND IT BECAME A COVER-UP.
THE TRIAL PROCEEDED
AS PLANNED,
BUT DID IT GO ON
WITH BRUNDIDGE?
THAT'S WHEN IT BECOMES
VERY INTERESTING.
THE CONFIDENTIAL FILES
OF FBI DIRECTOR J. EDGAR HOOVER
WERE OPENED IN 2005.
IN THOSE DOCUMENTS
BARBARA HAS FOUND
SOME ANSWERS FOR BILL.
LET ME PLAY FOR YOU
WHAT'S ON YOUR RECORD,
AND THEN WE HEAR A VOICE
YOU MAY RECOGNIZE.
Brundidge on recording:
I went back at the request
of the attorney general
last March,
and Rose willingly signed it.
I RECOGNIZE HIS VOICE.
THAT WAS MY UNCLE HARRY.
I TELL BILL
ABOUT HIS UNCLE'S ROLE
IN LINKING
THE REAL-LIFE IVA TOGURI
AND THE FABLED TOKYO ROSE.
THAT'S SAD, ISN'T IT?
YEAH.
HE PROBABLY DID MOST ANYTHING
TO GET A STORY,
AND THAT WAS A BIG STORY.
YOU'D WANTED TO KNOW
WHAT PART
HARRY BRUNDIDGE PLAYED
IN THIS TRIAL.
WHEN HE MENTIONED THAT
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL'S OFFICE
HAD SENT HIM BACK,
THAT'S WHERE THE STORY BECOMES
LARGER THAN JUST YOUR UNCLE.
SO WHAT WAS BRUNDIDGE'S ROLE
IN THE TRIAL?
WELL, BRUNDIDGE HAD NO ROLE
IN THE TRIAL.
THEY DIDN'T ALLOW HIM
TO TESTIFY.
THE FBI,
THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE:
HE WAS SUCH A HOT POTATO,
NOBODY WANTED TO GET NEAR HIM.
ON ONE INTERNAL MEMO,
BARBARA DISCOVERED
THAT J. EDGAR HOOVER
HAD WEIGHED IN
ON BRUNDIDGE'S
SO-CALLED WITNESS
RECANTING HIS TESTIMONY.
"I'M NOT SURPRISED
AT DEVELOPMENTS.
"IT WAS MOST UNWISE
FOR DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE
TO USE SUCH A PERSON AS
BRUNDIDGE IN THE FIRST PLACE."
THEY REALIZED THE WHOLE CASE
COULD BE BLOWN UP
IF HE TESTIFIED.
HE FINALLY WENT TO THE DEFENSE
AND OFFERED TO TESTIFY FOR THEM,
AND THEY WOULDN'T TOUCH HIM
EITHER.
GEE, THAT'S SOMETHING ELSE.
YOU KNOW, BACK IN WAR TIMES,
PEOPLE LOOKED UPON
THE JAPANESE REALLY BAD,
AND IT DIDN'T MAKE
ANY DIFFERENCE
WHETHER THEY WERE AMERICANS
OR --
LOOK AT ALL THE INTERNEES THEY
HAD, AND THEY WERE GOOD PEOPLE.
THEY WERE.
BILL, I REALLY WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR GIVING ME THIS RECORD
AND GIVING ME A CHANCE
TO SEE THIS LARGER HISTORY.
THANK YOU.
I'M GLAD ALL THIS CAME OUT.
I APPRECIATE THE WISDOM
WITH WHICH YOU HEARD THE STORY.
GIVEN THE NEW PUBLIC
DISCLOSURES
ABOUT IVA'S INNOCENCE
AND THE PERJURED TESTIMONY
AGAINST HER,
PRESIDENT FORD AGREED
TO LOOK INTO HER CASE.
IN HIS LAST OFFICIAL ACT
IN OFFICE,
HE GRANTED IVA TOGURI A FULL
AND UNCONDITIONAL PARDON
ON JANUARY 19, 1977.
SHE PASSED AWAY
IN 2006.
TWELVE AMERICANS
WERE TRIED FOR TREASON
AFTER WORLD WAR II.
SEVEN WERE RADIO BROADCASTERS.
AXIS SALLY WAS ONE OF
THE MOST INFAMOUS.
BORN MILDRED GILLARS, SHE DREAMT
OF BECOMING A STARLET.
WITH LITTLE THEATER SUCCESS,
GILLARS MOVED TO GERMANY
IN THE MID-1930s
AND WORKED FOR RADIO BERLIN.
FROM DECEMBER 1941
TO MAY 1945,
GILLARS' SULTRY VOICE
REACHED AMERICAN G.I.s
WITH PRO-GERMAN WAR UPDATES
DESIGNED TO DEPLETE MORALE.
GILLARS' BROADCASTS CAME UNDER
THE AUSPICES OF JOSEPH GOEBBELS,
HITLER'S PROPAGANDA MINISTER.
SHE POSED AS AN AMERICAN
RED CROSS VOLUNTEER,
INTERVIEWING AMERICAN P.O.W.s
BUT DISTORTING THEIR COMMENTS.
SHE CRITICIZED ROOSEVELT
AND CHURCHILL
AND MUSED ABOUT
THE UNFAITHFULNESS
OF G.I. WIVES AND GIRLFRIENDS
BACK HOME.
AXIS SALLY'S
MOST INFAMOUS BROADCAST,
"VISION OF INVASION,"
TARGETED AMERICAN TROOPS
AWAITING D-DAY.
GILLARS PLAYED A G.I. MOTHER
DREAMING OF HER SON'S DEATH.
CRIES OF THE WOUNDED
PLAYED IN THE BACKGROUND,
CREATING THE IMPRESSION
OF IMPENDING SLAUGHTER.
The boys will be killed
or crippled for the rest
of their lives.
AFTER THE WAR, GILLARS WAS
EXTRADITED TO THE U.S.
SHE WAS FOUND GUILTY
OF TREASON
AND SENTENCED TO 10 TO 30 YEARS
IN PRISON.
IN 1961, GILLARS LEFT JAIL
TO LIVE IN A CONVENT
AND TEACH CATHOLIC SCHOOL.
SHE DIED IN 1988.
Elyse:
OUR NEXT STORY GOES IN SEARCH
OF A NATIVE-AMERICAN LEGEND.
MORE THAN 125 YEARS
AFTER HIS DEATH,
THE NAME CRAZY HORSE
STILL ECHOES
IN THE BLACK HILLS
OF SOUTH DAKOTA.
IN LIFE, THE LAKOTA WARRIOR
AND SPIRITUAL MAN
VOWED TO PROTECT
THESE SACRED HUNTING GROUNDS
FROM ENCROACHING SETTLERS
AND GOLD MINERS.
IN 1876, HE HELPED CRUSH
THE U.S. CAVALRY TROOPS
OF GENERAL GEORGE CUSTER AT THE
BATTLE OF THE LITTLE BIGHORN.
BUT IS THIS A TRUE LIKENESS
OF THE WARRIOR?
DESPITE HIS FAME, CRAZY HORSE
REFUSED TO BE PHOTOGRAPHED,
SHUNNING WHITES
AND THEIR TECHNOLOGIES.
FOR YEARS, RUMORS
OF CRAZY HORSE PHOTOGRAPHS
HAVE TANTALIZED COLLECTORS.
MORE THAN 125 YEARS
AFTER THE WARRIOR'S DEATH,
TIM GIAGO
OF RAPID CITY, SOUTH DAKOTA,
HAS A FRAMED IMAGE
WHICH MAY BE
THE ONLY PHOTOGRAPHIC IMAGE
OF THIS LEGEND.
IT SAID, "TASUNKA WITKO,"
AND TASUNKA WITKO
IS THE LAKOTA NAME
THAT MEANS CRAZY HORSE.
I'M MEETING TIM AT HIS HOME
TO FIND OUT MORE.
HI.
WELCOME TO MY HOUSE.
THANK YOU.
WELL, ABOUT 27 YEARS AGO,
A CONSTRUCTION MANAGER CAME INTO
MY NEWSPAPER, THE LAKOTA TIMES,
AND HE HAD THIS WITH HIM.
ONE OF HIS EMPLOYEES,
A LAKOTA MAN,
HAD PUT IT IN HOCK
AND SAID HE COULD HAVE IT
IF HE WENT DOWN
AND TOOK IT OUT OF PAWN.
SO HE BROUGHT IT DOWN
TO MY NEWSPAPER.
ALONG WITH THAT WAS THIS LETTER
WHICH IS DATED 1904.
IT'S WRITTEN ENTIRELY
IN THE VERY OLD LAKOTA LANGUAGE.
IT SAYS THAT "TASUNKA WITKO,"
WHICH MEANS CRAZY HORSE.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW SPECIFICALLY
ABOUT CRAZY HORSE?
CRAZY HORSE WAS REALLY
ONE OF THE GREAT WARRIORS
OF THE LAKOTA.
PEOPLE SAID THAT BULLETS
COULDN'T HIT HIM.
ONE OF THE REASONS
HE'S SO ADMIRED AND LOVED
BY THE LAKOTA PEOPLE TODAY
IS HE WOULD NEVER SIGN A TREATY.
HE NEVER SOLD OUT ANY LAND
OR ANY OF HIS PEOPLE,
AND TO ME THAT'S
HIGHLY ADMIRABLE.
BUT WHAT CRAZY HORSE LOOKS LIKE
HAS LONG BEEN A MYSTERY.
DO YOU KNOW OF ANY OTHER
PHOTOGRAPHS OF CRAZY HORSE?
I'VE NEVER SEEN ONE.
I'VE SEEN PHOTOGRAPHS
THAT WERE DISPROVED,
THAT THAT'S NOT CRAZY HORSE,
ALWAYS PROVED TO BE
SOMEONE ELSE.
I WOULD LIKE YOU
TO FIND OUT VERY MUCH
WHETHER THIS IS INDEED
A TRUE PICTURE OF CRAZY HORSE.
[ ♪♪♪ ]
IT'S JUST AS TIM SUGGESTED.
THERE ARE A NUMBER
OF DISPUTED IMAGES
CLAIMING TO BE CRAZY HORSE.
MOST OF THEM HAVE
PRETTY SHAKY STORIES,
AND NONE RESEMBLE OUR GUY.
THERE'S NOTHING OBVIOUS
TO SUGGEST OUR MAN
IS EVEN A WARRIOR CHIEF,
NO WAR BONNET
OR ELABORATE DECORATION.
HE DOES HAVE A COLLAR ON
AND AN EAGLE FEATHER,
BUT BESIDES THAT,
HE'S DRESSED PRETTY PLAINLY.
I'M TRYING TO TAKE
THE BACK OFF CAREFULLY.
IT LOOKS LIKE THERE'S
MORE LAKOTA WRITING
ALONG WITH THE DATE, 1875.
AH, NOW, THIS IS HELPFUL.
HERE AGAIN, "CRAZY HORSE"
AND "1875" IN HANDWRITING.
BUT THERE'S ALSO
A STAMPED NAME AND ADDRESS.
"ALEX GARDNER, 921 PENNSYLVANIA
AVENUE, WASHINGTON, D.C."
LET ME DO SOME DIGGING.
THERE WAS AN ALEXANDER GARDNER
WHO WAS A CELEBRATED
PHOTOGRAPHER
IN THE 19th CENTURY.
HE PHOTOGRAPHED
ABRAHAM LINCOLN.
I'M NOT CERTAIN
THEY WERE THE SAME PERSON,
BUT ALEXANDER GARDNER
WAS A SCOTTISH SOCIALIST
WHO HAD GOTTEN INTERESTED
IN PHOTOGRAPHY
AFTER SEEING
MATTHEW BRADY'S WORK.
BRADY AND GARDNER BECAME
THE TWO BEST KNOWN
PHOTOGRAPHERS OF THE CIVIL WAR.
BUT IT SEEMS THAT A NUMBER
OF GARDNER'S BATTLEFIELD IMAGES
FROM THE WAR
WERE CONTROVERSIAL.
HE ACTUALLY MOVED BODIES
ON THE CIVIL WAR BATTLEFIELDS
TO BETTER SUIT
HIS PHOTOGRAPHIC NEEDS.
AND THIS IS INTERESTING:
GARDNER TRAVELED TO
THE LAKOTA TERRITORIES IN 1868
TO PHOTOGRAPH NEGOTIATIONS
BETWEEN NORTHERN PLAIN TRIBES
AND THE GOVERNMENT.
THE FORT LARAMIE TREATY
ESTABLISHED
THE GREAT SIOUX RESERVATION
AND PROTECTED THE BLACK HILLS
FOR THE LAKOTA.
IT'S POSSIBLE THAT THIS IS
AN ALEXANDER GARDNER PHOTOGRAPH
AND THAT GARDNER MET
CRAZY HORSE,
BUT THE DATE ON OUR PHOTO,
IF IT'S ACCURATE,
IS SEVEN YEARS AFTER
GARDNER PHOTOGRAPHED
THE LAKOTA TREATIES.
I THINK THE FIRST THING
THAT I NEED TO DO
IS FIGURE OUT EXACTLY
WHAT THIS NOTE SAYS.
I'M HEADED TO
OGLALA LAKOTA COLLEGE
IN RAPID CITY.
LAKOTA LANGUAGE AND CULTURE
PROFESSOR WILMER MESTETH
IS SKEPTICAL OF OUR IMAGE.
HE EXPLAINS WHY CRAZY HORSE
REJECTED PHOTOGRAPHY.
IN ORAL HISTORY THEY SAID
HE MADE A STATEMENT
THAT THESE PHOTOGRAPHS
WERE EVIL
AND THAT ANYBODY
THAT TOOK THEIR PHOTOGRAPH,
THEIR SOUL WAS CAPTURED
IN THE PICTURE.
CRAZY HORSE'S REJECTION
OF THE WHITE MAN'S TECHNOLOGY
WAS PART OF HIS DEFENSE OF THE
BESIEGED LAKOTA WAY OF LIFE.
THE 1868 TREATY
OF FORT LARAMIE
HAD GUARANTEED THE LAKOTA
THEIR TRIBAL LANDS,
BUT JUST SIX YEARS LATER,
THE TREATY WOULD BE VIOLATED.
IN 1874,
THERE WAS AN EXPEDITION
THAT CAME DOWN INTO THE
BLACK HILLS IN SEARCH OF GOLD,
LED BY GENERAL CUSTER,
AND THEY DID FIND GOLD
IN THE BLACK HILLS.
TWO YEARS LATER,
IN JUNE 1876,
CRAZY HORSE HELPED DEFEAT
GENERAL CUSTER
AT THE BATTLE
OF THE LITTLE BIGHORN.
IT WAS THE WORST U.S. MILITARY
DEFEAT OF THE INDIAN WARS.
ALTHOUGH MANY
SIOUX CONTEMPORARIES
WERE PHOTOGRAPHED,
THE LAKOTA HAVE RELIED
ON ORAL HISTORY
FOR A DESCRIPTION
OF CRAZY HORSE.
THEY SAID HE WAS
OF MEDIUM HEIGHT,
HIS HAIR WAS LIGHT IN COLOR,
AND HIS COMPLEXION WAS LIGHT.
AND HE HAD A MYSTERIOUS AURA
ABOUT HIM.
THEY SAID YOU COULD ALMOST FEEL
HIS PRESENCE AND HIS STRENGTH
AS A POWERFUL MAN.
THIS IS THE LETTER
THAT CAME WITH THE PHOTOGRAPH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THIS LETTER IS WRITTEN
IN OLD LAKOTA ORTHOGRAPHY,
IN LAKOTA LANGUAGE.
WILMER TELLS ME THAT OLD LAKOTA
WAS USED FOR A HUNED YEARS,
UNTIL ABOUT 1960.
[ reading in Lakota ]
"THIS PHOTOGRAPH IS
A PHOTOGRAPH OF CRAZY HORSE."
WHAT ELSE DOES IT SAY?
[ reading in Lakota ]
"THE WAY YOU WOULD RECOGNIZE
THAT THIS IS HE
IS THERE IS A SCAR
ON HIS LEFT CHEEK."
IS IT TRUE THAT CRAZY HORSE
HAD A SCAR?
YES, CRAZY HORSE WAS SHOT
BY A MAN CALLED NO WATER
IN A JEALOUS RAGE.
HE SHOT TO KILL CRAZY HORSE
BUT GRAZED HIM ON THE LEFT SIDE
OF THE CHEEK.
THE MAN ON THE PHOTO
IS FAVORING HIS RIGHT.
IF THERE'S A SCAR ON THE LEFT,
I CAN'T TELL.
THEN IT SAYS, "WE WERE WITH
CRAZY HORSE WAY BACK THEN.
THIS IS ME, DEWEY BEARD."
WILMER THINKS THAT
DEWEY BEARD
MAY HAVE DICTATED THE STORY
TO SOMEONE,
POSSIBLY TO THIS B.B.E.
SIGNED AT THE BOTTOM.
AND WHO WAS DEWEY BEARD?
DEWEY BEARD WAS THERE
AT THE LITTLE BIGHORN
AT THE AGE OF 10 YEARS OLD.
AND POSSIBLY KNEW
CRAZY HORSE.
I'M PRETTY SURE THIS PERSON
KNEW CRAZY HORSE, YES.
IN YOUR OPINION, DO YOU THINK
THERE'S ANY POSSIBILITY
THAT THIS COULD BE
CRAZY HORSE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
THIS PERSON IN THIS PHOTOGRAPH
IS OF DARKER COMPLEXION.
CRAZY HORSE HIMSELF
WAS LIGHT-COMPLECTED.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT
TO MAKE OF THIS.
WILMER THINKS THE NOTE
IS LEGITIMATE.
STILL, HISTORY'S VERDICT
STANDS IN OUR WAY.
NOBODY'S EVER PRODUCED A
PHOTOGRAPH OF CRAZY HORSE, EVER.
WILMER SUGGESTED I VISIT
THE CRAZY HORSE MEMORIAL
IN THE BLACK HILLS.
SCULPTOR KORCZAK ZIOLKOWSKI
BEGAN THE MASSIVE CARVING
IN THE 1940s...
AND TODAY IT REMAINS
THE WORLD'S LARGEST
MOUNTAIN SCULPTURE
IN PROGRESS.
THE MONUMENT IS A TESTAMENT TO
THE IMPORTANCE OF HIS MEMORY,
BUT WHERE IS THE PHYSICAL MODEL
FOR THE MASSIVE FACE?
DOUG WAR EAGLE IS
CRAZY HORSE'S GRANDSON.
HOW WAS THE MONUMENT BUILT?
I MEAN, HOW DO WE KNOW
WHAT HE LOOKS LIKE?
IT'S JUST THE CLOSEST REPLICA
OF HIM.
THERE NEVER WAS A PHOTO
EVER TAKEN OF OUR GRANDFATHER.
HE SAYS THE MONUMENT REPRESENTS
CRAZY HORSE'S SPIRIT
RATHER THAN HIS EXACT IMAGE.
WHEN I SHOW DOUG OUR PHOTO,
RIGHT AWAY HE'S SKEPTICAL.
THIS MAN HAS AN EAGLE FEATHER
IN HIS HAIR.
OUR GRANDFATHER NEVER WORE
AN EAGLE FEATHER IN HIS HAIR.
OUR GRANDPA WEARS
THE RED-TAILED HAWK FEATHER
WITH THE BUFFALO BONE.
DOUG'S BROUGHT SOMETHING
TO SHOW ME
THAT FEW OUTSIDE HIS FAMILY
HAVE SEEN.
I'VE BROUGHT TWO SKETCHES
OF OUR GRANDFATHER'S.
THE FIRST ONE IS WAGLULA,
OLD MAN CRAZY HORSE.
HE SAYS THE WARRIOR
CRAZY HORSE
WAS ACTUALLY THE THIRD MAN
TO CARRY THAT NAME.
IN ACCORDANCE
WITH LAKOTA TRADITION,
CRAZY HORSE INHERITED THE NAME
FROM THIS MAN, HIS FATHER,
WHEN HE BECAME A WARRIOR.
AND THE OTHER SKETCH I HAVE HERE
IS OF THE WARRIOR.
IT WAS SKETCHED LONG AFTER
HIS DEATH IN 1934,
WHEN CRAZY HORSE'S
YOUNGER SISTER
DESCRIBED HIS APPEARANCE
TO A FORENSIC ARTIST.
THE LIKENESS TRIGGERED
AN EMOTIONAL REACTION.
SHE CRIED, BECAUSE SHE SAID
THAT'S THE CLOSEST LIKENESS
THAT YOU WILL EVER HAVE
OF HIM.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
WELL, HE CERTAINLY DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE OUR PHOTOGRAPH.
SO IT HAS THE TWO FEATHERS,
THE LONG, FLOWING HAIR,
AND A LITTLE BIT
OF A SCAR.
THAT'S THE CLOSEST
WE'LL EVER GET
OF OUR GRANDFATHER,
THE WARRIOR,
THE ONE THAT FOUGHT
THE BATTLE OF LITTLE BIGHORN.
DOUG IS CONVINCED OUR IMAGE
ISN'T CRAZY HORSE.
BUT THIS SKETCH
WAS MADE BY SOMEONE
WHO NEVER MET CRAZAZY HORSE,
SIX DECADES AFTER HE DIED.
I'M TAKING THE IMAGE
TO THE SMITHSONIAN,
WHICH HOUSES
THE WORLD'S LARGEST ARCHIVE
OF NATIVE-AMERICAN PHOTOGRAPHS.
I WANT TO SHOW IT TO ONE
OF THE SMITHSONIAN'S CURATORS.
BUT FIRST,
BECAUSE THERE HAVE BEEN
MANY BOGUS
CRAZY HORSE PICTURES,
WHILE I'M HERE,
I ALSO WANT TO SHOW IT
TO STAFF PHOTOGRAPHER
DON HURLBURT.
WELCOME TO THE DARKROOM.
WOW.
OKAY, SO HERE'S MY PIECE,
AND ON THE BACK IT SAYS 1875.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU THOUGHT
IT WAS PERIOD.
IT DEFINITELY HAS
CHARACTERISTICS
FROM THAT TIME FRAME.
IT'S YELLOWING, IT'S GOT
A GOOD GOLD TONE TO IT.
IT HAS THE SHININESS
ON THE SURFACE OF THE PRINT
THAT A MODERN PRINT
WOULD NOT HAVE
BUT PRINTS OF THAT AGE DO.
HOW WOULD A PRINT LIKE THIS
HAVE BEEN MADE IN THE 1870s?
IT WAS DEFINITELY A MULTI-DAY,
MULTI-STEP PROCESS
TO MAKE ONE OF THESE PRINTS.
THESE GUYS DID A LOT OF WORK
TO GET THESE PHOTOGRAPHS.
THESE PRINTS CAME
FROM GLASS PLATE NEGATIVES
THAT WERE MADE, PRODUCED FROM
ABOUT THE 1850s TO 1880s.
WELL, I CAN SHOW YOU.
THE INVENTION OF GLASS PLATES
MEANT THAT FOR THE FIRST TIME,
PHOTOGRAPHERS LIKE GARDNER
HAD A PHOTOGRAPHIC MEDIUM
FROM WHICH TO MAKE
UNLIMITED NUMBERS OF PRINTS.
GLASS PLATES REVOLUTIONIZED
PHOTOGRAPHY.
NOW THAT I'VE CLEANED IT
AND CHECKED IT,
WE'RE GOING TO BRING IT
OVER HERE, SET IT DOWN,
GET A SHEET OF MODERN PAPER OUT,
BECAUSE WE DO NOT HAVE
ANY OF THE ALBUMEN PAPER
WITH US ANYMORE.
DON SAYS GARDNER, OR WHOEVER
TOOK THE PHOTOGRAPH,
WOULD HAVE MADE
ALBUMEN SILVER PRINTS,
WHICH EXPOSED
IN SUNLIGHT.
TODAY, USING MODERN
PHOTO PAPER,
DEVELOPING A PRINT IN THE
DARKROOM TAKES MERE MINUTES.
THAT'S GREAT.
I LEARN MORE ABOUT THE PRINT
FROM FORMER ARCHIVIST
AND SMITHSONIAN VOLUNTEER
PAULA FLEMING.
SHE SAYS THE IMAGE WAS ALMOST
CERTAINLY TAKEN BY GARDNER
NOT OUT WEST
BUT ON THE EAST COAST
AT THE ADDRESS
ON THE BACK OF OUR PHOTOGRAPH.
HE HAD A STUDIO
IN WASHINGTON, D.C.,
AND HE TOOK MOST OF HIS
INDIAN PORTRAITS THERE.
WELL, WHAT WOULD BRING THEM
TO WASHINGTON, D.C.?
AFTER THE CIVIL WAR,
THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT
RENEWED ITS EFFORTS
TO DEAL WITH THE INDIANS
TO RESOLVE ISSUES OF LAND
ACQUISITION AND ANNUITIES.
PAULA SAYS HUNDREDS
OF AMERICAN INDIANS
WERE INVITED TO WASHINGTON
AS TRIBAL DELEGATIONS.
THE GOVERNMENT WANTED
TO SHOW THE INDIANS
THE BENEFITS OF CIVILIZATION,
SO THEY TOOK THEM ON TRAINS
AND THEY TOOK THEM TO BIG CITIES
TO SHOW THEM WHAT IT WAS LIKE
TO BE CIVILIZED.
ON THE SURFACE,
THE WASHINGTON VISITS
WERE EFFORTS TO PEACEFULLY
RESOLVE LAND DISPUTES
AND DEMONSTRATE
THAT THE INDIANS
WERE BEING TREATED
RESPECTFULLY,
BUT PAULA SAYS THE VISITS
OFTEN INCLUDED A STOP
WHICH HAD A POLITICAL AGENDA.
THEY WOULD ALSO TAKE THEM
TO THE ARSENAL
AND THEY'D SHOW THEM
STOCKPILES
OF WEAPONS AND CANNONBALLS
AND THEY WOULD HAVE DISPLAYS
OF MILITARY MIGHT.
THE GOVERNMENT WANTED
TO SHOW THEM
THAT IT WAS ACTUALLY FUTILE
TO FIGHT FOR THEIR LANDS.
THEY WERE GOING TO LOSE?
THEY WERE GOING TO LOSE.
CRAZY HORSE'S GRANDSON
HAD TOLD ME
THAT THE CLOTHING
AND DECORATION IN OUR IMAGE
WAS NOT TYPICAL
FOR THE WARRIOR.
BUT PAULA SAYS NOT ALL THE
PHOTOGRAPHS TAKEN IN WASHINGTON
WERE WHAT THEY APPEARED TO BE.
SOME PHOTOGRAPHERS
ACTUALLY KEPT PROPS
TO MAKE SURE THAT THE INDIANS
LOOKED EXOTIC ENOUGH,
AND SOMETIMES THEY PUT
THE IMPROPER COSTUMES
ON THE WRONG CULTURES.
PAULA HAS A SURPRISE FOR ME.
WITH THOUSANDS OF PHOTOGRAPHS
IN THE ARCHIVES,
IT CAN BE A LITTLE DAUNTING
IF YOU DON'T HAVE A NAME.
BUT I DID A LITTLE BIT
OF RESEARCH, AND COME HERE,
I'VE GOT SOMETHING
TO SHOW YOU.
WOW!
IT'S A GLASS PLATE NEGATIVE,
JUST LIKE THE ONE
DON SHOWED ME.
IT'S THE EXACT SAME IMAGE.
SURE IS.
THIS NEGATIVE WAS USED
TO PRINT THAT IMAGE.
IS IT CRAZY HORSE?
WHAT PAULA TELLS ME NEXT
CLOSES THE CASE.
WELL, TIM, IT WAS
AN INCREDIBLE INVESTIGATION.
I TELL HIM HE HAS AN AUTHENTIC
ALEXANDER GARDNER PHOTO,
ONE OF THE NATION'S
MOST CELEBRATED
PERIOD PHOTOGRAPHERS.
THERE ARE A LOT OF EXPERTS
THAT DON'T BELIEVE
THAT CRAZY HORSE
WAS EVER PHOTOGRAPHED,
AND THAT MADE IT
REALLY DIFFICULT.
FINALLY, THOUGH,
I WAS ABLE TO IDENTIFY
THE MAN IN YOUR PHOTOGRAPH
BY TRAVELING
TO WASHINGTON, D.C.,
JUST LIKE HE DID
150 YEARS AGO.
THERE WAS AN ENGLISHMAN BY THE
NAME OF WILLIAM HENRY BLACKMORE,
AND HE COMMISSIONED GARDNER
TO PHOTOGRAPH
THE DELEGATIONS OF INDIANS.
AND HE ALSO PUBLISHED
THE IMAGES.
THAT'S OUR GUY.
THE MAN IN THE PHOTOGRAPH
IS VUA-SHA-PEH,
WHOSE ENGLISH NAME
IS STABBER,
AND HE WAS AN OGLALA LAKOTA
WHO CAME TO WASHINGTON, D.C.,
WITH RED CLOUD
ON A DELEGATION.
THE MAN IN THIS PHOTOGRAPHED
HAD WITNESSED
ONE OF THE LAST
PEACEFUL NEGOTIATIONS
BETWEEN THE LAKOTA
AND THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT
BEFORE GOLD WAS DISCOVERED
IN THE BLACK HILLS.
HE WAS AN IMPORTANT PART
OF LAKOTA HISTORY.
I THINK IT'S GREAT
THAT WE KNOW WHO HE IS NOW.
VUA-SHA-PEH HAD TRAVELED
TO WASHINGTON
WITH RED CLOUD
AND THE LAKOTA DELEGATION.
IN CONTRAST, CRAZY HORSE
REJECTED DIPLOMACY
AND DEFENDED LAKOTA TRADITIONS
AS A WARRIOR TO THE END.
EXPERTS SAY THAT HE NEVER WENT
TO WASHINGTON;
HE STAYED ON HIS LAND
TO FIGHT FOR HIS PEOPLE
AND TO FIGHT
THE U.S. MILITARY.
I'M A GREAT ADMIRER
OF CRAZY HORSE,
AND I REALLY HOPED
THAT THIS WAS HIM.
WELL, I GUESS WE'LL NEVER KNOW
WHAT CRAZY HORSE LOOKED LIKE.
I HOPE THAT I CAN TAKE
THE PHOTOGRAPH
AND FIND HIS DESCENDANTS
AND PASS THE PHOTOGRAPH
DOWN TO THEM.
WE THANK YOU FOR COMING
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE
TO GIVE US THE NEWS.
AFTER HIS VICTORY
AT THE LITTLE BIGHORN,
CRAZY HORSE FOUGHT ON
UNTIL THE SPRING OF 1877.
THEN, HIS PEOPLE WEAKENED
BY WAR AND HUNGER,
HE SURRENDERED
AT CAMP ROBINSON, NEBRASKA.
ON SEPTEMBER 5, 1877,
HE WAS ARRESTED AND BROUGHT
INTO THE GUARD HOUSE.
REALIZING HE WAS
ABOUT TO BE LOCKED UP,
CRAZY HORSE STRUGGLED
AND WAS STABBED
BY A SOLDIER
WITH A BAYONET.
HE DIED LATE THAT NIGHT,
AND SOON AFTER,
HIS BODY WAS RETURNED
TO HIS ELDERLY PARENTS.
TO THIS DAY, HIS FINAL
BURIAL PLACE IS UNKNOWN,
BUT HIS SPIRIT LIVES ON
IN THE BLACK HILLS.
REPATRIATION RAISES
COMPLEX ISSUES
ABOUT CULTURAL HERITAGE
AND WHO OWNS IT.
TODAY, LITERALLY MILLIONS
OF AMERICAN INDIAN ARTIFACTS
ARE HOUSED IN NON-NATIVE MUSEUMS
AND PRIVATE COLLECTIONS.
MANY OF THESE OBJECTS, LIKE
TOOLS, WEAPONS, AND CLOTHES,
WERE ACQUIRED THROUGH
PERFECTLY LEGAL MEANS.
OTHERS, HOWEVER, WERE BOUGHT
FOR PENNIES OR STOLEN.
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT SAW
NOTHING WRONG WITH THIS,
SINCE ITS OFFICIAL POSITION
ON THE TRIBES
WAS TO TRY TO ASSIMILATE THEM
INTO THE MAINSTREAM.
BUT NATIVE PEOPLES
ARE STILL WITH US,
AND SOME HAVE BEGUN TO ASK FOR
-- EVEN DEMAND --
THEIR MOST IMPORTANT
ARTIFACTS BACK.
SO IN 1990, THE U.S. GOVERNMENT
SIGNED INTO LAW
THE NATIVE AMERICAN
GRAVE PROTECTION
AND REPATRIATION ACT,
OR NAGPRA.
NAGPRA REQUIRES
FEDERALLY FUNDED ORGANIZATIONS
TO RETURN SKELETONS AND OBJECTS
OF CULTURAL PATRIMONY
TO TRIBAL REPRESENTATIVES
IF THEY FOLLOW
THE CORRECT PROCEDURES.
NAGPRA ONLY APPLIES TO
FEDERALLY FUNDED ORGANIZATIONS.
PRIVATE COLLECTIONS
OR MUSEUMS ABROAD
DON'T FALL UNDER
ITS JURISDICTION.
DESPITE THESE CHALLENGES,
BOTH THE TRIBES AND MUSEUMS
SEE NAGPRA AS A STEP FORWARD.
Wes:
IN AN ENCORE PRESENTATION,
OUR FINAL STORY TURNS THE PAGES
OF A LONG-LOST DIARY
FROM A WORLD WAR II
BOMBER PILOT.
DECEMBER 13, 1943:
THE U.S. ARMY AIR FORCE
445th BOMB GROUP
ATTACKS ENEMY SHIPYARDS
BENEATH THE SKIES
OF KIEL, GERMANY.
IT'S THEIR FIRST
OF 280 AIR-RAID MISSIONS
INSIDE A NEW BOMBER
CALLED THE B-24 LIBERATOR.
THE BOMBER IS
THE ALLIES' GREAT HOPE,
FLYING FARTHER, LONGER,
AND CARRYING MORE BOMBS
DEEP INTO HITLER'S
GERMANY.
NOT A SINGLE PLANE IS LOST
ON THIS MISSION,
BUT THE 445th WILL RARELY
BE SO LUCKY AGAIN.
THE LIBERATOR EARNS ITSELF
ANOTHER MORE OMINOUS NICKNAME:
THE FLYING COFFIN,
DUE TO THE HIGH CASUALTY RATE
AMONG B-24 PILOTS.
WHY WERE THESE MISSIONS
SO DEADLY,
AND WHAT CONVINCED THEIR CREW
TO ACCEPT SUCH TERRIBLE ODDS?
SIXTY YEARS AFTER THE LAST
OF THOSE MISSIONS,
JIM CHAPMAN
OF LEXINGTON, NORTH CAROLINA,
HAS A DIARY THAT MAY REVEAL
NEW INFORMATION
ABOUT THESE PLANES AND MEN
WHO HELD HITLER AT BAY.
I'M WES COWAN,
AND I'M HEADING TO MEET JIM.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS DIARY.
MY DAD BROUGHT THIS
HOME WITH HIM
AFTER HE FINISHED
HIS TOUR OF DUTY
DURING WORLD WAR II.
AND THE OBVIOUS QUESTION
TO ME IS,
IT'S NOT YOUR DAD'S DIARY.
THAT'S CORRECT.
THE DIARY BELONGED TO HIS
CO-PILOT NAMED WILLIAM MORAN.
BOTH SERVED ON A B-24.
BOTH MEN FLEW PLANES
IN THE 445th BOMB GROUP
STATIONED IN
TIBENHAM, ENGLAND.
HOW DID YOUR DAD
GET IT?
WELL, THAT'S
A GOOD QUESTION.
I ACTUALLY DISCOVERED
THE DIARY
IN A BOX
OF MY FATHER'S MEMENTOS.
HE DISCOVERED IT AFTER
HIS FATHER DIED 20 YEARS AGO.
CAN YOU READ ME
SOME ENTRIES?
YES, I'D BE GLAD TO.
"SURE DREADED GOING,
"ESPECIALLY AFTER I FOUND
THE TARGET TO BE HAMBURG.
"FELT SURE
I WOULDN'T GET BACK.
"AT LEAST I KNOW NOW THAT
I'LL BE ABLE TO FACE DEATH
"WHEN MY TIME COMES.
"THE ONLY THING THAT I FEARED
WAS LEAVING JAYNE.
I ADORE HER EVERY BREATH."
MARY JAYNE
WAS MORAN'S WIFE.
IT'S THESE PERSONAL DETAILS
IN THE DIARY THAT HAUNT JIM.
"MAY 9, 1944.
"AN AIRMAIL LETTER
FROM MY ANGEL.
"MY BABY IS PRETTY SURE
SHE IS PREGNANT.
"THANK GOD!
"BOUGHT THE BOYS BEER
WITH MY LAST SIX SHILLINGS
TO CELEBRATE."
THAT'S REALLY GREAT.
THERE'S SOMETHING IMPORTANT
MISSING FROM THIS DIARY:
AN ENDING.
THE LAST ENTRY IS
FROM OCTOBER 29th,
SEVEN MONTHS BEFORE THE END
OF THE WAR IN EUROPE.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
WELL, WES, I'D LIKE TO FIND OUT
WHAT HAPPENED TO BILL MORAN,
IF HE CAME BACK HOME
OR IF HE WAS KILLED.
I'D LIKE TO REALLY KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM.
JIM IS EAGER
TO KNOW MORE ABOUT
WHAT THE MEN HIS FATHER FLEW
WITH SAW AND DID
DURING THEIR TIME
IN ENGLAND.
AND HE WANTS HELP
WITH ANOTHER QUESTION, TOO.
I WOULD LIKE TO BE ABLE
TO REUNITE THE DIARY
WITH BILL MORAN'S FAMILY.
I THINK IT'S VERY IMPORTANT
FOR THE FAMILY TO HAVE THIS.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE
THE DIARY WITH ME,
AND I'M READY TO GET GOING.
WELL, LET'S SEE.
EVERY TIME I READ ONE
OF THESE SOLDIER'S DIARIES,
I JUST GET THE SENSE
THAT I'M HOLDING A PIECE
OF HISTORY IN MY HAND.
THE DIARY COVERS
ABOUT A YEAR,
FROM OCTOBER 1943
TO OCTOBER 1944.
MUCH OF IT
IS WRITTEN MECHANICALLY,
MORE LIKE A LOG
THAN A PERSONAL JOURNAL.
BUT IT'S CLEAR HIS UNIT IS
IN THE THICK OF THE ACTION.
HERE'S ONE,
SEPTEMBER 27th.
"STARTED A LETTER
TO MY ANGEL,
"BUT BAHN STOPPED IN
TO TELL ME
"OUR SQUAD LOST
FOUR OUT OF NINE.
IT WAS WITHEY'S LAST ONE."
A LOT OF BOMBERS WENT DOWN
WITH MEN MORAN KNEW.
IF HE'S SHAKEN BY THIS,
I WOULDN'T KNOW IT
FROM THE MATTER-OF-FACT
LANGUAGE.
AND HERE'S BILL MORAN'S
LAST ENTRY,
OCTOBER 29, 1944.
MORE DEATH AND MORE
MATTER-OF-FACT LANGUAGE.
BILL WRITES,
"MASS AND COMMUNION.
"PUT A COUPLE HOURS
ON A SHIP.
"HEARD A ROTTEN GERMAN BROADCAST
LATE LAST NIGHT
CALLING EISENHOWER
A RAT."
BUT THERE ARE NO CLUES
WHY MORAN STOPPED WRITING.
DID HE GO BACK HOME OR WAS
HIS NEXT MISSION FATAL?
THERE ARE PLENTY
OF NAMES HERE.
MAYBE SOMEONE BILL MORAN
WROTE ABOUT IS STILL ALIVE
AND CAN FILL IN
THESE BLANK PAGES FOR ME.
"LENNY," IT LOOKS LIKE.
"GOLDEN."
"CHAPPY, PELTON, AND I
WERE LUCKY NOT TO GO."
I'LL CALL MY OFFICE AND ASK
THEM TO TRY TO TRACK DOWN
SOME OF BILL MORAN'S
WAR BUDDIES.
WES COWAN.
BILL OLDSON.
GLAD TO MEET YOU, WES.
WHILE THEY'RE SEARCHING,
I'VE COME TO FLORIDA
TO MEET WITH PROFESSOR
WILLIAM OLDSON
FROM THE INSTITUTE
ON WORLD WAR II
AND THE HUMAN EXPERIENCE.
HERE'S THE DIARY THAT I SENT YOU
THE TRANSCRIPT OF.
OH, NICE.
VERY UNUSUAL COVER.
AND IF I MUST SAY,
HIS HANDWRITING'S
BETTER THAN MOST, TOO.
WILLIAM SAYS UNEARTHING
JOURNALS FROM THE BATTLEFRONT
IS ALWAYS
AN IMPORTANT DISCOVERY,
A UNIQUE WINDOW ON THE MEN
WHO ACTUALLY DID THE FIGHTING.
IT'S THE UNVARNISHED TRUTH,
AND IT'S THE YARDSTICK YOU CAN
HOLD UP TO EVERYTHING ELSE --
TO THE LETTERS HOME,
TO THE PROPAGANDA,
TO THE NEWSREEL --
AND SAY, "HERE'S
WHAT HE FELT."
AND THERE CERTAINLY WAS
A LOT TO WRITE ABOUT.
WILLIAM EXPLAINS THAT
IN 1943,
ALLIED BOMBING RAIDS ON GERMANY
ARE OFTEN INEFFECTUAL
AT HITTING MILITARY
AND INDUSTRIAL TARGETS.
BUT BY 1944, WITH FORD CRANKING
OUT A NEW B-24 EVERY HOUR,
THE AMERICAN BOMBERS
ARE SUCCESSFULLY TARGETING
HITLER'S FACTORIES
AND FUEL SUPPLIES
AND HELPING TURN THE WAR
IN THE ALLIES' FAVOR.
BUT THE CARNAGE AMONG
FLIGHT CREWS IS HORRENDOUS.
IN '43, WE LOST
OVER 3,000 PLANES.
'44, WE LOSE
OVER 11,000 PLANES.
WILLIAM BELIEVES
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
MORAN WAS KILLED
OVER GERMANY.
FLYING DAYLIGHT RAIDS
MADE THE BOMBERS EASY PREY
FOR GERMAN FIGHTER PLANES
AND ANTI-AIRCRAFT GUNS.
IF YOU WERE FLYING
WITH BRITISH BOMBER COMMAND,
YOU HAD A 65% CHANCE
OF BEING A CASUALTY.
IF YOU'RE FLYING IN
THE AMERICAN 8th AIR FORCE,
YOU'VE GOT A 40% TO 60% CHANCE
OF BEING A CASUALTY.
IF YOU'RE LUCKY ENOUGH TO BE
IN THAT KAMIKAZE SQUADRON,
YOU'VE ONLY GOT A 53% CHANCE
OF BEING A CASUALTY.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
WHILE LOGISTICS PROBLEMS
OFTEN KEPT JAPANESE KAMIKAZE
SQUADRONS GROUNDED,
IN EUROPE,
THE BIG ALLIED BOMBERS
WERE SEEING COMBAT
ALMOST DAILY.
SO A KAMIKAZE PILOT
WHO'S SUPPOSED TO KILL HIMSELF
STOOD A BETTER CHANCE
OF SURVIVING
THAN A B-24 BOMBER PILOT?
HARD TO BELIEVE,
ISN'T IT?
WILLIAM SAYS THE OFTEN REMOTE,
MATTER-OF-FACT LANGUAGE
IN SUCH WARTIME WRITING
WAS A WAY OF WALLING OFF
OR ESCAPING
THE HORROR
OF EVERYDAY LIFE.
I THINK IT'S NOT ONLY TYPICAL,
IT'S NECESSARY.
THEY CAN'T BROOD
ABOUT IT.
IT'S GOING TO INTERFERE
WITH THEIR OWN PERFORMANCE,
IT'S GOING TO DEPRESS THEM.
THE WRITING IS A FORM
OF SELF-DEFENSE.
WHAT'S UNUSUAL
ABOUT THE DIARY YOU HAVE
IS THE ROMANTIC ASPECT
OF IT.
I DON'T KNOW ANY OTHER DIARY
THAT I'VE SEEN
WHERE SOMEBODY'S REFERRING
TO HIS WIFE AS "ANGEL."
AND WE HAVE LOTS OF LETTERS
WHERE IT SAYS, "HELLO, HONEY,"
OR SOMETHING OF THAT SORT,
BUT NOT IN THE DIARIES.
THANKS VERY MUCH
FOR SHARING THIS WITH ME.
THANK YOU FOR LETTING ME
SEE THIS.
THIS IS A VERY SPECIAL
DOCUMENT.
I STILL DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHY
BILL MORAN STOPPED WRITING
IN THE JOURNAL,
BUT MY OFFICE
HAS BEEN ABLE
TO TRACK DOWN
HIS MILITARY RECORDS,
AND THEY'VE SENT THEM
TO ME AT THE LIBRARY.
IT'S SOBERING NEWS.
ON OCTOBER 31, 1944,
BILL MORAN WAS FLYING
WITH PILOT EDWARD SPEERS
AND SIX OTHER MEN
WHEN THEIR PLANE DISAPPEARED.
THIS REPORT
OF AIRCRAFT ACCIDENT
OR MISSING AIRCRAFT REPORT
CONFIRMS THAT MORAN WAS KILLED
IN SOME SORT OF
A TRAINING ACCIDENT.
THEY'RE NOT CLEAR EXACTLY
WHAT HAPPENED.
HE TOOK OFF
IN THE FORMATION.
AFTER HE TOOK OFF,
NOBODY ELSE IN THE AIRCRAFT
FORMATION EVER SAW HIM AGAIN.
THE WRECKAGE AND MORAN'S BODY
ARE NEVER FOUND.
THIS TOOK PLACE TWO DAYS AFTER
THE LAST ENTRY IN HIS DIARY.
MARY JAYNE WAS SEVEN MONTHS
PREGNANT WHEN BILL DIED.
IF I'M GOING TO HELP JIM RETURN
THE JOURNAL TO BILL'S FAMILY,
I'M GOING TO NEED HELP
TRACKING DOWN HIS DESCENDANTS.
MY OFFICE HAS LOCATED
JACK PELTON,
ONE OF MORAN'S BUDDIES
MENTIONED IN THE DIARY.
HEY, JACK.
HEY, WES.
JACK AGREES TO MEET ME
AT THE AMERICAN AERO SERVICES
HANGAR IN FLORIDA,
WHERE THE COLLINGS FOUNDATION
MAINTAINS A B-24 BOMBER.
BOY, THIS IS QUITE A PIECE
OF MACHINERY, ISN'T IT?
OH, IT REALLY IS,
IT'S A WONDERFUL AIRPLANE.
AND YOU WERE A PILOT
OF ONE OF THESE BIRDS.
I WAS A PILOT,
FLEW 32 MISSIONS.
HOW'D YOU LIKE TO GET UP
IN THE COCKPIT?
LOVE TO.
OH, WONDERFUL.
IT'S BEEN MORE THAN 50 YEARS
SINCE JACK'S TAKEN A SEAT
AT THE CONTROLS.
SO WHAT WAS IT LIKE
TO FLY ONE OF THESE BABIES?
IT WAS VERY EXCITING,
REALLY.
JACK TELLS ME
IN ORDER TO ATTACK
HEAVILY DEFENDED TARGETS,
PILOTS LIKE HE
AND BILL MORAN FLEW
AT ALTITUDES
OVER 20,000 FEET,
WHERE TEMPERATURES REACHED
MINUS 30 DEGREES.
SO IT WAS COLD,
YOU'RE WEARING AN OXYGEN MASK.
THERE ARE NO HYDRAULICS
IN THESE STEERING WHEELS.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
A HELL OF A JOB.
IT WAS A STRANGE FEELING.
YOU WERE
IN ANOTHER WORLD.
JACK EXPLAINS THAT
THE LIGHTWEIGHT FRAME
THAT MADE THE B-24
SUCH AN EFFICIENT BOMBER
ALSO MADE IT VULNERABLE
TO ENEMY FIRE.
WE BROUGHT ONE PLANE HOME
WITH 153 HOLES IN IT.
[ machine gun firing ]
BULLETS AND SHELLS
FROM GERMAN FIGHTER PLANES
TORE THROUGH
THE AMERICAN AIRCRAFT
AND HELPED EARN THE B-24
ITS REPUTATION
AS A FLYING COFFIN.
YOU KNOW, I'VE GOT
BILL MORAN'S DIARY HERE.
WHAT KIND OF A GUY
WAS BILL MORAN?
WHAT WAS HE LIKE?
BILL MORAN WAS
A GREAT CO-PILOT,
GREAT SENSE OF HUMOR,
IRISHMAN ALL THE WAY.
JACK HAS A PICTURE
OF BILL AND MARY JAYNE,
BILL'S PREGNANT WIFE,
TAKEN RIGHT BEFORE
THE AIRMAN LEFT THE STATES.
SO THAT'S BILL.
BILL.
THAT'S MARY JAYNE.
AND LOOK AT THEM
HOLDING HANDS THERE.
I'D RECOGNIZE YOU
ANYWHERE.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU GUYS
ARE HAVING A LOT OF FUN.
YEAH, WE DID,
HAD A GREAT EVENING.
LAST TIME WE SAW OUR WIVES
FOR A YEAR.
ONE MORE QUESTION:
WHERE WAS BILL MORAN FROM?
PITTSBURGH, PENNSYLVANIA.
MARY JAYNE WAS FROM THERE,
TOO, THEN?
YES, SHE WAS.
WHAT EVER HAPPENED TO
MARY JAYNE, DO YOU KNOW?
I DON'T KNOW.
I TRIED TO FIND HER
WHEN I GOT BACK IN THE STATES,
COULD NOT.
ONE TIME WHEN I WAS
ON BUSINESS IN PITTSBURGH,
I HEARD SHE WAS THERE,
BUT I STILL COULDN'T
TRACK HER DOWN.
SO I'M BACK
AT THE LIBRARY
TO SEARCH THROUGH
GENEALOGICAL RECORDS.
AT FIRST, I DRAW A BLANK
LOOKING FOR MARY JAYNE.
MAYBE I CAN GET INFORMATION
FROM ANOTHER FAMILY MEMBER.
I FINALLY GET A BREAK
WITH THE SOCIAL SECURITY
DEATH INDEX
FOR BILL'S MOTHER VERONICA.
BINGO, HERE SHE IS.
SHE DIED IN MARCH 1967
IN MIAMI, FLORIDA.
HER OBITUARY
EVENTUALLY LEADS US
TO THE NAMES OF TWO
OF BILL'S SURVIVING SISTERS:
ADELAIDE YOUNG
AND JEANIE KIMBROW
OF SEBRING, FLORIDA.
IF THERE'S A LOCAL LISTING,
MAYBE WE'RE IN BUSINESS.
IT TAKES A WHILE,
BUT EVENTUALLY I GET LUCKY.
ADELAIDE YOUNG,
THERE'S HER PHONE NUMBER,
ADDRESS,
BORN AUGUST 1930.
IT'S GOT TO BE HER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'VE FOUND
A LIVING RELATIVE.
HELLO, MRS. YOUNG?
ADELAIDE IS EXCITED
BY NEWS OF THE DIARY,
AND WE MAKE PLANS
TO MEET.
YOU KNOW WHY
I'VE COME TO SEE YOU.
YES.
I HAVE A DIARY THAT WAS WRITTEN
BY YOUR BROTHER.
OH, "MY LIFE
IN THE SERVICE."
DO YOU RECOGNIZE
THAT HANDWRITING?
OH, OF COURSE.
IT'S THE CONSTANT REFERENCES
TO BILL'S WIFE
THAT CATCH ADELAIDE'S EYE.
HE ALWAYS SPEAKS OF HER
IN SUCH A GENTLE WAY.
YOU GET THE SENSE THAT
THEY WERE REALLY IN LOVE.
OH, FROM THE TIME
THEY MET.
ADELAIDE WAS 14
WHEN HER BROTHER DIED.
THE TELEGRAM WAS LAYING
ON THE DINING ROOM TABLE,
AND WE KEPT SAYING, "THEY'LL
FIND HIM, THEY'LL FIND HIM.
SOMEDAY THEY'LL FIND HIM."
THERE WAS NEVER ANY
MEMORIAL SERVICE OR ANYTHING
BECAUSE "SOMEDAY
THEY'LL FIND HIM."
AT FIRST THE VERY PREGNANT
MARY JAYNE
WASN'T EVEN TOLD
HER HUSBAND WAS MISSING.
SHE LEARNED BILL
HAD BEEN KILLED
FROM A FRIEND
WHO VISITED HER
RIGHT AFTER SHE'D GIVEN BIRTH
TO THEIR DAUGHTER.
SHE WAS INCONSOLABLE.
SHE WAS JUST
UNBELIEVABLY IN GRIEF.
MARY JAYNE DIED ROUGHLY
20 YEARS AFTER HER HUSBAND,
BUT WHAT ADELAIDE
REVEALED NEXT
WILL BE EXTRAORDINARY NEWS
FOR JIM.
THIS HAS BEEN
AN INCREDIBLE STORY FOR ME.
I TELL JIM ABOUT SOME OF
THE THINGS I'VE LEARNED
WHILE WORKING
ON BILL'S DIARY.
I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU, THOUGH,
THAT I HAVE SOME BAD NEWS.
I LET JIM KNOW THAT BILL MORAN
DIED IN A TRAINING MISSION
AND HIS WIFE PASSED AWAY
OVER 40 YEARS AGO,
BUT THE STORY
DOESN'T END THERE.
THERE'S SOMEONE I DO
WANT YOU TO MEET,
SO IF YOU WANT TO FOLLOW ME,
WE'LL GO MEET THAT PERSON.
I'D LIKE TO DO THAT.
ADELAIDE TOLD ME
THAT THE BABY
THAT BILL WAS
SO EAGERLY EXPECTING
WAS BORN 32 DAYS
AFTER HE DIED.
HER NAME WAS JANIE.
SHE'S MARRIED.
SHE HAS TWO CHILDREN
AND FOUR GRANDCHILDREN.
BILL MORAN WOULD HAVE BEEN
A GREAT-GRANDFATHER.
HEY, GUYS.
HI.
I WANT YOU TO MEET SOMEBODY,
JIM.
THIS IS JIM CHAPMAN.
THIS IS CHAPPY'S SON.
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
THIS IS ADELAIDE YOUNG.
THIS IS BILL'S SISTER.
I REMEMBER HIM
TALKING ABOUT --
OH, HI, ADELAIDE.
HE TALKED ABOUT BILL CHAPMAN
ALL THE TIME.
OH, IT'S SO NICE
TO MEET YOU.
OH, I'M SO GLAD
AND THIS IS BILL'S DAUGHTER,
JANIE.
HI, JIM,
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
THANK YOU FOR TAKING CARE
OF THE JOURNAL.
I'M SO GLAD
TO HAVE FOUND YOU.
THANKS TO JIM,
BILL MORAN'S THOUGHTS
ARE NOW FINALLY GOING HOME
TO THE DAUGHTER
HE NEVER KNEW.
I JUST FEEL LIKE I KNOW
SO MUCH ABOUT YOU ALREADY.
[ clears throat ]
EXCUSE ME.
SORRY.
THE DIARY'S BEEN IN OUR FAMILY
FOR 63 YEARS.
WHAT WAS SO FASCINATING
WAS READING IN THE DIARY
ABOUT YOUR MOTHER
CARRYING YOU
AND YOUR DAD BEING
SO HAPPY AND EXCITED
ABOUT YOUR MOM
BEING PREGNANT.
IN THE DIARY ITSELF,
IT JUST COMES THROUGH
THAT HE LOVES YOUR MOTHER
VERY MUCH.
MORAN AND HIS FELLOW PILOTS
HAD HELPED DEAL HITLER'S
WAR MACHINE A CRIPPLING BLOW,
AND THEIR CHILDREN
AND CHILDREN'S CHILDREN
WOULD LIVE IN A WORLD
THEY HAD TRANSFORMED.
THIS IS A GLIMPSE
INTO YOUR FATHER'S LIFE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, JIM,
FOR TREASURING IT
AND TAKING CARE OF IT
FOR ALL THOSE YEARS.
TO HEAR MORE ABOUT
JACK PELTON'S EXPERIENCES
AS A WORLD WAR II
BOMBER PILOT,
VISIT HISTORY DETECTIVES
ON THE WEB AT pbs.org.
Tukufu:
BILL MORAN ALSO WROTE
IN HIS DIARY
ABOUT THE KASSEL MISSION.
IT'S THE BIGGEST SINGLE LOSS
FOR AN AMERICAN BOMBER GROUP
IN THE COUNTRY'S
MILITARY HISTORY.
"WEDNESDAY,
SEPTEMBER 27, 1944.
"BAHN STOPPED IN TO TELL ME
THAT WE LOST 22 OUT OF 35 SHIPS.
"WITHEY, GOLDEN, BOECHER,
ROBINSON, AND REYNOLDS
DIDN'T GET BACK."
JACK PELTON REMEMBERS
THAT DAY WELL.
THEY CALLED ME
FOR THAT MISSION
AND I HAD A PASS
TO GO TO LONDON.
AND I SHOWED THE SERGEANT
MY PASS, AND HE SAID, "OKAY,"
TOOK THE GUY
IN THE NEXT BUNK,
AND HE NEVER CAME HOME.
THIRTY-NINE PLANES
FROM THE 445th BOMB GROUP
SET OUT TO ATTACK A TANK FACTORY
IN KASSEL, GERMANY.
BUT THE LEAD PLANE
MAKES A WRONG TURN,
AND THE 445th
GETS SEPARATED
FROM THE REST
OF THE COMBAT WING.
ALONE OVER ENEMY TERRITORY,
THE LIBERATORS ARE AMBUSHED
BY OVER 100 GERMAN FIGHTERS.
IN LESS THAN FOUR MINUTES,
116 AMERICAN PILOTS ARE DEAD.
SURVIVORS RETURNING TO BASE
RECOUNT THE HORROR.
THE AIR WAS FILLED
WITH BOMBERS BLOWING UP
AND FALLING BOMBER PARTS,
PARACHUTES, AND BODIES,
AND BODY PARTS.
IT WAS A REAL HOLOCAUST.
SOME OF THE GUYS CAME BACK,
THEY WERE ALMOST HYSTERICAL.
THEY COULD HARDLY
CONTAIN THEMSELVES.
THOUGH THE LOSS IS TRAGIC,
THE WAR GOES ON.
THE NEXT DAY, THE MILITARY
SENDS ANOTHER BOMBER GROUP
BACK TO KASSEL
TO FINISH THE JOB.
ALL OF THOSE PLANES
RETURNED SAFELY.
HISTORY DETECTIVES WILL RETURN
IN A MOMENT, BUT FIRST...
Tukufu:
BE A HISTORY DETECTIVE
YOURSELF.
GO TO pbs.org
AND LEARN MORE ABOUT
INVESTIGATIVE TECHNIQUES
OR SUBMIT YOUR OWN MYSTERY
TO THE TEAM.
YOU CAN ALSO FIND OUT MORE
ABOUT TONIGHT'S INVESTIGATIONS
ONLY AT pbs.org.
THIS EPISODE OF HISTORY
DETECTIVES IS AVAILABLE ON DVD.
THE COMPANION BOOK TO
THE PROGRAM IS ALSO AVAILABLE.
TO ORDER,
CALL PBS HOME VIDEO AT...
OR VISIT US ONLINE AT...
Captions by LNS Captioning
Portland, Oregon
www.LNScaptioning.com
Elvis Costello:
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ IT'S JUST LIKE
WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
Gwendolyn:
THIS PROGRAM WAS MADE POSSIBLE
BY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO YOUR PBS STATION
FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.
Elyse:
WE'RE THE HISTORY DETECTIVES,
AND WE'RE GOING TO INVESTIGATE
SOME UNTOLD STORIES
FROM AMERICA'S PAST.
THIS WEEK, WHAT CAN THIS
WE'RE THE HISTORY DETECTIVES,
AND WE'RE GOING TO INVESTIGATE
SOME UNTOLD STORIES
FROM AMERICA'S PAST.
THIS WEEK, IS THIS
A MISSING MURDER WEAPON
FROM THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY
MASSACRE?
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SHOOT IT?
Tukufu:
DID THE FATHER
OF JOHN WILKES BOOTH
THREATEN TO ASSASSINATE
A SITTING PRESIDENT?
SOMEONE HAS WRITTEN
"ANONYMOUS."
IS IT BY JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
OR NOT?
THERE'S NO QUESTION, JUNIUS
BRUTUS BOOTH WAS INSANE.
Wes:
DID THIS METAL BOMB EXPLODE
A MORBID BLACK MARKET TRADE
IN 19th-CENTURY OHIO?
FIRE IN THE HOLE!
Elvis Costello:
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ I GET SO ANGRY
WHEN THE TEARDROPS START ♪
♪ BUT HE CAN'T BE WOUNDED
'CAUSE HE'S GOT NO HEART ♪
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ IT'S JUST LIKE
WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
Gwendolyn:
THIS PROGRAM WAS MADE POSSIBLE
BY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO YOUR PBS STATION
FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.
Elyse:
OUR FIRST STORY
INVESTIGATES A WEAPON
THAT MAY HAVE BEEN FIRED
IN ONE OF THE NATION'S
MOST INFAMOUS CRIMES.
FEBRUARY 14, 1929,
ST. VALENTINE'S DAY:
GANGSTERS TURN A DAY
OF LOVE AND REFLECTION
INTO A BLOODBATH,
EXECUTING SEVEN MEN
IN A CHICAGO GARAGE.
[ machine gun firing ]
AUTHORITIES SUSPECT THE HAND
OF POWERFUL GANGSTER AL CAPONE,
WHO WAS FIGHTING TO CONTROL THE
CITY'S ILLEGAL LIQUOR TRADE.
THE DAYLIGHT KILLING
OUTRAGES THE NATION
AND BECOMES A SYMBOL
OF THE FAILURE OF PROHIBITION.
HOWEVER, NO ONE IS EVER
CONVICTED OF THE KILLING
AND THE CRIME
REMAINS UNSOLVED.
NOW MIKE LUX
OF LAKE GENEVA, WISCONSIN,
BELIEVES HE HAS
THE MISSING WEAPON
FROM THIS LEGENDARY
GANGLAND MASSACRE.
THIS GUN MAY HAVE TAKEN
THE LIVES OF TWO MEN.
I'M ON MY WAY TO MEET MIKE
AND LOOK INTO HIS STORY.
VERY NICE TO MEET YOU.
OH, WOW!
12-GAUGE SHOTGUN.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT IT.
AND WHAT'S THE STORY BEHIND IT?
IT WAS SUPPOSEDLY USED IN THE
ST. VALENTINE'S DAY MASSACRE.
THAT WAS IN CHICAGO
IN 1929.
YES.
YOU KNOW, JUST BY LOOKING
AT THE GUN,
TO ME IT KIND OF LOOKS
LIKE THE BARREL
IS NOT PERIOD TO THE PIECE.
CORRECT.
I HAD THIS BARREL PUT ON
TO MAKE IT LEGAL.
ORIGINALLY THE BARREL WAS CUT
OFF PROBABLY ABOUT RIGHT HERE.
AND I ACTUALLY HAVE
A COUPLE PICTURES OF IT.
OH, AND I CAN SEE
THE BARREL'S MUCH SHORTER.
MIKE TELLS ME THAT
SHORT-BARREL SHOTGUNS
ARE FEDERALLY REGULATED
AND THAT HE PUT A LONGER BARREL
ON THE GUN
TO COMPLY WITH THESE RULES.
HOW'D YOU GET THE GUN?
I HAD INHERITED IT FROM
MY FATHER WHEN HE PASSED AWAY.
MIKE SAYS HIS FATHER
GOT THE GUN
FROM A FORMER CHICAGO FIRE
COMMISSIONER, ROBERT QUINN.
MIKE BELIEVES THAT QUINN,
WHO IS NOW DECEASED,
MAY HAVE USED HIS INFLUENCE
TO SECRETLY ACQUIRE THE GUN.
I THINK WHEN QUINN
ACQUIRED IT,
IT HAD TO HAVE BEEN
IN THE MID-'70s.
MIKE'S FATHER WAS KILLED
IN AN AIR CRASH IN 1979.
TWO DAYS LATER, ONE OF
HIS FRIENDS TALKED TO ME,
AND HE WAS VERY UPSET
ABOUT THE PLANE CRASH,
BUT HE WAS ALSO VERY WORRIED
THAT NOW I OWN THIS PIECE
AND HE DIDN'T WANT ME
TO BE SHOWING IT OFF
OR TELLING ANYBODY ABOUT IT,
AND I HAVEN'T.
THAT'S WHY I'VE HAD IT
FOR 30 YEARS HIDDEN AWAY.
WHAT'D YOU THINK WHEN YOUR DAD
TOLD YOU THAT THIS WAS USED
IN THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY
MASSACRE?
I THOUGHT, "COME ON,
YOU'RE PULLING MY LEG."
AND HE WAS DEAD SERIOUS.
AND HE WAS A SERIOUS
KIND OF GUY.
WHEN IT CAME TO WEAPONS
LIKE THIS IN HIS COLLECTION,
HE WAS NOT FOOLING.
MIKE, WHAT EXACTLY
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW?
IF IT TRULY IS THE SHOTGUN
THAT WAS USED
AT THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY
MASSACRE.
I WILL SEE WHAT I CAN
FIND OUT.
DO YOU MIND IF I SIT HERE
FOR A WHILE AND EVALUATE IT?
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I USED TO WORK IN THE GUN
DEPARTMENT AT CHRISTIE'S,
SO I KNOW A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT GUNS.
AND THE FIRST THING
I NEED TO DETERMINE
WAS IF THIS GUN
WAS EVEN AROUND IN 1929.
WAS IT PERIOD TO THE TIME
OF THE MASSACRE?
IT CERTAINLY APPEARS TO BE.
THE WOODEN FORESTOCK
IS FOR A REPEATING,
OR PUMP-ACTION,
SHOTGUN.
THAT MEANS IT CAN FIRE
MULTIPLE SHOTS
WITHOUT RELOADING.
I KNOW THAT THERE IS
A SERIAL NUMBER HERE.
AH, HERE IT IS:
18514 B.
THAT MAY HELP US
MORE PRECISELY DATE THE GUN,
ALTHOUGH BACK THEN
I'M PRETTY CERTAIN A PURCHASER
WAS NOT REQUIRED
TO REGISTER THEIR WEAPON.
I SEE THAT IT SAYS
"WESTERN FIELD" ON THE PLATE.
YOU KNOW, I DID NOTICE SOMETHING
UNUSUAL OVER HERE ON THE STOCK.
THERE ARE TWO NOTCHES.
MAYBE WE COULD GET SOME
INFORMATION FROM THAT AS WELL.
IF THIS GUN REALLY WAS USED
IN THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY
MASSACRE,
THEN IT'S AN EXCEPTIONAL PIECE
OF HISTORY
AND ITS COLLECTION VALUE
WOULD BE VERY HIGH.
ON THE MORNING
OF FEBRUARY 14, 1929,
SEVEN IMMACULATELY DRESSED MEN
GATHERED IN A GARAGE
ON CHICAGO'S NORTH SIDE.
SOME WERE MEMBERS
OF A GANG
LED BY THE NOTORIOUS BOOTLEGGER
BUGS MORAN.
WITHOUT WARNING,
GUNMEN STORMED IN
AND UNLEASHED A HAIL OF BULLETS
THAT LEFT ALL SEVEN DEAD.
WITNESSES REPORTED SEEING
WHAT LOOKED LIKE TWO POLICE
OFFICERS LEAVE THE GARAGE.
THE MID-MORNING SLAUGHTER
TURNED THE MEDIA SPOTLIGHT
ON THE CITY OF CHICAGO AND THE
VIOLENT STRUGGLE BEING WAGED
OVER CONTROL
OF THE ILLEGAL LIQUOR TRADE.
I'M IN CHICAGO TO MEET
THE AUTHOR OF THIS BOOK,
ART BILEK.
HI, ART.
HERE IS THE GUN.
TELL ME YOUR OPINION ON THAT.
WHAT DO I HAVE HERE?
IT'S A 12-GAUGE SHOTGUN...
ART IS ALSO
A FORMER POLICE OFFICER
AND FAMILIAR WITH THE WEAPONS
OF CHOICE OF CRIMINALS.
MOST IMPORTANTLY,
IT HAS A SAWED-OFF STOCK.
GANGSTERS IN THE 1920s
HAD THESE STOCKS MODIFIED
SO THAT THEY COULD CARRY THESE
UNDER THEIR OVERCOATS LIKE THIS.
SO IT'S A GANGSTER GUN?
OH, YES.
IN FACT, THAT'S THE WAY I WOULD
REFER TO IT, AS A GANGSTER GUN.
ART SAYS EXACTLY HOW
THE VICTIMS
WERE LURED TO THEIR DEATH
WAS NEVER ESTABLISHED.
INVESTIGATORS SUSPECTED
THE PHONY POLICEMEN
WERE AL CAPONE GANG MEMBERS.
WHEN THEY ORDERED
THE RIVAL GANGSTERS
TO LINE UP AND TURN AROUND,
MORE CAPONE MEN ENTERED,
CARRYING WEAPONS.
WE DON'T KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT WENT ON
EXCEPT TWO OF THE MEN PULLED OUT
THOMPSON SUBMACHINE GUNS
AND BEGAN RIDDLING THE BACK
OF THESE SEVEN MEN
WITH MACHINE GUN BULLETS.
GETTING INFORMATION ABOUT THE
CRIME WAS ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE.
THE CHICAGO UNDERWORLD
WAS RULED BY FEAR.
BEFORE DYING, ONE OF
THE VICTIMS, FRANK GUSENBERG,
TOLD INCREDULOUS POLICE,
"NOBODY SHOT ME."
INVESTIGATORS TURNED
TO EVIDENCE
FROM THE BLOOD-DRENCHED GARAGE.
SERGEANT JAMES LOFTUS, WHO WAS
THE FIRST OFFICER ON THE SCENE,
WAS ABLE TO COLLECT FROM
THE SCENE SEVERAL ITEMS.
HERE IS A COPY
OF THE INVENTORY REPORT
THAT HE FILED THAT VERY DAY.
THERE WERE SEVERAL .45-CALIBER
SHELLS AND BULLETS,
THE SIZE OF AMMUNITION USED
IN THE TOMMY GUN.
ART POINTS OUT SOMETHING
OF PARTICULAR INTEREST.
AND THERE IS THE ITEM
RIGHT THERE:
TWO SHOTGUN SHELLS, 12-GAUGE.
THAT'S THE SAME GAUGE
AS MIKE'S GUN.
I TELL ART THAT MIKE BELIEVES
HIS WEAPON ONCE BELONGED
TO ROBERT QUINN, A FORMER
CHICAGO FIRE COMMISSIONER
IN THE 1950s
THROUGH THE 1970s.
HE WAS ONE OF THE MORE NOTABLE
FIRE COMMISSIONERS
IN THE HISTORY OF CHICAGO.
HE SAYS QUINN WAS PART OF AN
INNER CIRCLE AROUND THE MAYOR
IN A PERIOD
WHEN CONTROL OF EVIDENCE,
ESPECIALLY FOR
A CELEBRATED COLD CASE,
WAS NOT NEARLY
AS TIGHTLY HELD AS TODAY.
DO YOU THINK THAT HE COULD
HAVE OWNED THIS GUN?
HE KNEW ALL OF
THE TOP OFFICIALS.
HE WOULD HAVE KNOWN
THE CORONER VERY WELL.
AND HE WOULD HAVE KNOWN OTHER
PEOPLE IN THE POLICE DEPARTMENT.
IT'S ENTIRELY POSSIBLE
THAT ONE WAY OR ANOTHER
HE MIGHT HAVE MET A MAN
THAT HAD POSSESSION OF THIS GUN.
ART SAYS THE DESCRIPTION
OF TWO OF THE KILLERS
DRESSED IN POLICE UNIFORMS
TURNED UP THE HEAT
ON INVESTIGATORS,
BUT IT WASN'T UNTIL TEN MONTHS
LATER THAT THEY CAUGHT A BREAK:
AN AL CAPONE ASSOCIATE
NAMED FRED "KILLER" BURKE
WAS INVOLVED IN A FENDER BENDER
ACROSS STATE LINES IN MICHIGAN.
WELL, THERE WAS A POLICE OFFICER
ON THE NEXT CORNER,
AND HE BEGAN WALKING DOWN.
WITH THAT, KILLER BURKE
DRIVES OFF,
THE POLICEMAN JUMPS
ON THE RUNNING BOARD,
BURKE TAKES OUT HIS GUN
AND SHOOTS HIM.
THE OFFICER TUMBLES
TO THE GROUND DEAD.
A HUGE MANHUNT FOLLOWS,
AND THAT'S HOW THEY FOUND
BURKE'S CAR OVERTURNED
WHERE HE TRIED TO MAKE
A TURN IN THE ROAD AND FAILED.
ART EXPLAINS THAT BURKE WAS
A CAREER GANGSTER AND HIT MAN.
A WORLD WAR I VET, HE WAS
SUSPECTED OF INTRODUCING
THE THOMPSON SUBMACHINE GUN
TO THE DETROIT MOB,
HELPING MURDER THREE MEN
IN 1927.
IN THE AFTERMATH OF THE
ST. VALENTINE'S DAY KILLINGS,
BURKE WAS HOLED UP
IN A SMALL MICHIGAN TOWN.
AFTER KILLING THE OFFICER,
POLICE RAIDED HIS HIDEOUT.
AND UPSTAIRS ON THE SECOND
FLOOR, THEY OPENED A CLOSET
AND THERE WERE THE TWO
MACHINE GUNS, A SHOTGUN,
AND SOME OTHER
ARMORY-TYPE DEVICES.
FORENSIC ANALYSIS
WOULD LATER CONNECT
SOME OF FRED BURKE'S WEAPONS
TO THE MASSACRE.
WHERE ARE THOSE GUNS NOW?
THE GUNS AT THE CURRENT TIME
ARE BEING HELD
BY THE BERRIEN COUNTY, MICHIGAN,
SHERIFF'S OFFICE,
WHERE THEY WERE RECOVERED
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I'M IN BERRIEN COUNTY TO MEET
WITH LIEUTENANT KEITH HAFER,
THE WEAPONS EXPERT IN CHARGE
OF THE MASSACRE GUNS.
WOW.
THESE ARE THE TWO THOMPSON
SUBMACHINE GUNS USED
IN THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY
MASSACRE.
LIEUTENANT HAFER EXPLAINS
THAT FOR YEARS,
THE GUNS WERE HELD
BY THE FBI
AT THEIR BALLISTICS CRIME LAB
IN QUANTICO, VIRGINIA.
IN THE LATE 1970s, A MICHIGAN
DETECTIVE TRAINING WITH THE FBI
SPOTTED THE GUNS
AND ASKED FOR THEIR RETURN.
ARE THESE THE ONLY GUNS
THAT YOU HAVE?
THERE WERE OTHER GUNS SEIZED
FROM FRED BURKE'S HOME,
BUT THOSE GUNS ARE LONG GONE
AND I HAVE NO RECORD OF THEM.
WELL, I'M INVESTIGATING
THIS SHOTGUN
THAT I BELIEVE MAY HAVE BEEN
USED AT THE MASSACRE.
IT'S CERTAINLY THE RIGHT AGE
AND IT LOOKS LIKE
A GANGSTER GUN.
WHAT I NOTICE IMMEDIATELY
ARE THESE TWO NOTCHES
CUT INTO THE PISTOL GRIP
OF THIS SHOTGUN.
LIEUTENANT HAFER SAYS
CRIMINALS SOMETIMES CARVED
NOTCHES ON THEIR WEAPONS
WHEN THEY KILLED A MAN.
AND THE THOMPSONS
THAT WE HAVE
HAVE NOTCHES CARVED
INTO THE TRIGGER GUARDS.
HE'S NOT SURE
IF THE MARKINGS
CAN CONNECT OUR GUN
TO THE MASSACRE,
BUT OFFERS TO TAKE ME
TO THE FIRING RANGE
TO SHOW EXACTLY WHY OUR GUN
AND THE TOMMY GUN
WOULD HAVE BEEN FAVORITE
GANGSTER WEAPONS.
FIRE!
HIT HIM RIGHT IN THE CHEST,
KEEP GOING.
THE TOMMY GUN
CAN FIRE CONTINUOUSLY.
LIEUTENANT HAFER HAS TOLD ME TO
FIRE JUST THREE SHOTS AT A TIME
BECAUSE THE WEAPON
IS DIFFICULT TO CONTROL.
IT'S PRETTY POWERFUL.
LIEUTENANT HAFER SAYS
THIS MODEL TOMMY GUN
COULD UNLOAD A DEVASTATING
700 ROUNDS A MINUTE.
I CAN UNDERSTAND WHY
A GANGSTER LIKES THAT GUN.
IT WAS THE HIGH-TECH WEAPON
OF ITS DAY.
HE TELLS ME THAT BEFORE THE
INTRODUCTION OF THE TOMMY GUN
TO THE CHICAGO CRIME WORLD
IN 1924,
THE REPEATING SHOTGUN WAS
THE GANGSTER GUN OF CHOICE.
WHAT YOU HAVE HERE IS
A PUMP-ACTION REPEATING SHOTGUN,
WHICH WAS A VERY COMMON AND
DEVASTATING WEAPON OF THE TIME.
OUR GUN IS CAPABLE OF FIRING
SIX SHOTS BEFORE RELOADING,
UNLEASHING A DEVASTATING SPRAY
OF SHOTGUN PELLETS.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SHOOT IT?
YEAH, DEFINITELY.
PULL IT IN TIGHT,
YEP.
AIM AT YOUR TARGET
AND SHOOT WHEN READY.
[ gunshots and reloading ]
WOW, THAT'S GOT QUITE
A KICK TO IT.
WHY DON'T YOU OPEN THE BOLT
AND LET'S MAKE SURE IT'S EMPTY.
OKAY.
NOW, DO YOU THINK
THAT THIS GUN WAS USED
IN THE ST. VALENTINE MASSACRE?
IT'S CERTAINLY A POSSIBILITY.
LIEUTENANT HAFER SUGGESTS
I PICK UP THE SHELL CASINGS.
IF OUR GUN WAS USED
IN THE MASSACRE,
THE SHELLS MAY BEAR
USEFUL FORENSIC INFORMATION.
HE'S NOT SURE WHAT REMAINS
IN THE OLD POLICE FILES
BUT SUGGESTS I SPEAK WITH
POLICE HISTORIAN CHRISS LYON
AT THE HERITAGE MUSEUM AND
CULTURAL CENTER IN ST. JOSEPH.
HI, CHRISS.
HI, ELYSE.
GREAT TO MEET YOU,
WELCOME TO ST. JOSEPH, MICHIGAN.
THANK YOU.
CHRISS SAYS THE POLICE FOUND A
TROVE OF INCRIMINATING EVIDENCE
WHEN THEY RAIDED
FRED BURKE'S HIDEOUT.
THIS ONE IS ONE
OF THE ORIGINAL PHOTOS
OF SOME OF THE WEAPONRY
THAT WAS FOUND
IN FRED BURKE'S HOUSE.
OKAY, SO I SEE HERE
THE TWO TOMMY GUNS
THAT WERE FOUND IN HIS HOUSE.
AND THIS IS ALL THE ARSENAL.
AND THIS MUST BE THE SHOTGUN.
CHRISS EXPLAINS HOW THE CHICAGO
AUTHORITIES HAD TURNED
TO A FORENSICS EXPERT
NAMED CALVIN GODDARD
TO EXAMINE THE BURKE WEAPONS.
WHEN GODDARD TOOK THESE GUNS
TO BE TESTED BALLISTICALLY,
HE TOOK THE TOMMY GUNS
AND HE TOOK THIS GUN,
WHICH IS A 20-GAUGE.
NOW, WE KNOW THAT THERE
WAS A 12-GAUGE USED
IN THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY
MASSACRE
BY THE SHELLS THAT WERE FOUND.
SO IF THIS GUN WASN'T USED
IN THE MASSACRE,
THEN IT'S STILL POSSIBLE
THAT OUR GUN WAS.
I'M CURIOUS, HAD GODDARD ALSO
EXAMINED THE 12-GAUGE SHELLS
FOUND AT THE CRIME SCENE
AFTER THE MASSACRE?
CHRISS SUGGESTS
I SPEAK WITH
FORMER CRIME LAB DIRECTOR
PAUL DOUGHERTY,
WHO HAS STUDIED THE MASSACRE
AND THE SUBSEQUENT
POLICE DETECTIVE WORK.
OKAY, SO HERE'S THE GUN
I TALKED TO YOU ABOUT.
YES.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THIS IS A WESTERN FIELD,
WHICH IS MADE BY STEVENS.
IT HAS A FAIRLY LOW
SERIAL NUMBER,
WHICH INDICATES
IT'S FAIRLY OLD.
PAUL SAYS THE MODEL WAS IN
PRODUCTION FROM 1905 TO 1932
AND PERIOD TO THE MASSACRE.
HOWEVER, HE CAN'T PRECISELY
DATE THE GUN
BECAUSE THE MANUFACTURER'S
SERIAL RECORDS
HAVE BEEN DESTROYED.
SO TELL ME A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT GODDARD.
WELL, CALVIN GODDARD
WAS A FIRST-CLASS SCIENTIST
AND HE APPROACHED EVERYTHING
THAT HE DID AS A SCIENTIST.
PAUL SAYS GODDARD TRAINED
AS A PHYSICIAN,
BUT IN 1926, ENTERED
THE EMERGING FIELD
OF BALLISTIC SCIENCE.
HIS FORENSIC WORK,
WHICH HELPED CONVICT
ANARCHIST NICOLA SACCO
IN THE CELEBRATED SACCO
AND VANZETTI MURDER CASE,
CAUGHT THE ATTENTION
OF THE CHICAGO CORONER.
IT WAS THE ENORMITY OF
THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY MASSACRE
THAT BROUGHT THE NEED
FOR SCIENTIFIC CRIME DETECTION
TO THE PUBLIC ATTENTION
AND TO THE ATTENTION
OF AUTHORITIES OF CHICAGO.
GODDARD TEST-FIRED
THE BURKE RAID TOMMY GUNS
AND COMPARED THE SHELLS
TO THOSE
FROM THE SCENE OF THE CRIME.
HE EXPLAINED TO
THE CHICAGO INVESTIGATORS
HOW SPENT SHELLS HAD
THEIR OWN IDENTIFYING MARKS.
HE WOULD PUT THE CARTRIDGE CASES
UNDER THE COMPARISON MICROSCOPE,
ONE ON EITHER SIDE.
THEN HE COMPARED THEM
THROUGH THE EYEPIECE,
WHICH IS HERE.
SO, PAUL, TELL ME
WHAT I'M LOOKING AT.
USING A REPLICA
OF GODDARD'S MICROSCOPE,
PAUL TELLS ME TO COMPARE
THE IMPRESSIONS ON TWO SHELLS
FROM GODDARD'S
PERSONAL COLLECTION.
SO THE FIRING PIN IMPRESSIONS
ARE THE SAME.
BY MATCHING
FIRING PIN IMPRESSIONS,
GODDARD DETERMINED THAT
FRED BURKE'S TOMMY GUNS
WERE USED IN THE MASSACRE.
SO THESE CAME
FROM THE SAME GUN.
WELL, I HAVE THESE SHELLS,
AND I SHOT THESE SHELLS
FROM MIKE'S GUN.
PAUL OFFERS TO TAKE
A CLOSER LOOK.
ALTHOUGH THE CARTRIDGE SHELLS
FROM THE CRIME SCENE
ARE LONG GONE, HE SAYS
GODDARD DID EXAMINE THEM
AND TESTIFIED IN FRONT
OF THE CORONER'S GRAND JURY.
THE CHARACTERISTICS
THAT GODDARD EMPHASIZED
IN HIS TESTIMONY, THOUGH,
WERE THE EXTRACTOR
AND EJECTOR MARKS.
EXTRACTOR MARKS ARE
THE MARKINGS THAT OCCUR
WHEN A SHELL IS
IN THE CHAMBER OF A GUN
AND IS EXTRACTED
FROM THE CHAMBER,
AND AN EJECTOR MARKING OCCURS
WHEN THE SHELL IS KICKED OUT
OF THE GUN.
WE TAKE A CLOSE LOOK
AT OUR SHELLS.
OH, THOSE TWO LITTLE SCRATCHES?
THAT IS CORRECT.
I SEE THEM.
WHAT PAUL TELLS ME NEXT
IS CERTAINLY GOING TO BE
OF INTEREST TO MIKE.
INVESTIGATORS FOUND
BULLETS AND SHELLS
AT THE SCENE OF THE CRIME,
AND TWO OF THOSE SHELLS
WERE FROM A 12-GAUGE SHOTGUN,
THE SAME GAUGE
AS YOUR SHOTGUN.
THAT GETS US VERY CLOSE.
I TELL MIKE THAT THE STRANGE
CARVED NOTCHES ON HIS WEAPON
COULD HAVE BEEN
A GANGSTER SIGNATURE,
INDICATING THE WEAPON
HAD BEEN USED IN A MURDER.
SIMILAR MARKINGS
HAD ALSO BEEN SEEN
ON THE THOMPSON SUBMACHINE GUNS
USED IN THE MASSACRE.
ALTHOUGH MISSING EVIDENCE
MADE A DIRECT COMPARISON
WITH HIS SHELLS
IMPOSSIBLE TODAY,
AT THE TIME OF THE MASSACRE,
THE EXPERT BROUGHT IN
BY THE AUTHORITIES
HAD CONDUCTED A THOROUGH
FORENSIC INVESTIGATION.
GODDARD DID CLOSELY EXAMINE
THE SHELLS THAT WERE FOUND
AT THE SCENE OF THE CRIME,
AND HE MADE A PRETTY
INTERESTING DISCOVERY.
THESE ARE THE TYPES
OF MARKINGS
THAT GODDARD FOUND ON THE SHELLS
FROM THE SCENE OF THE CRIME.
GODDARD HAD DETERMINED
THAT THE SHOTGUN USED
IN THE MURDER OF SEVEN MEN
ON ST. VALENTINE'S DAY, 1929,
WAS A PUMP-ACTION GUN, TOO,
THE SAME AS MIKE'S.
SO IN YOUR OPINION,
COULD THIS GUN HAVE BEEN USED
IN THE MASSACRE?
YES.
IT IS THE RIGHT VINTAGE.
IT HAS BOTH THE EXTRACTOR
AND EJECTOR MARKINGS
WHICH GODDARD IDENTIFIED.
WE CAN PROVE THAT THE GUN
THAT WAS SHOT THAT DAY
WAS A 12-GAUGE
REPEATING SHOTGUN.
YOUR GUN IS A 12-GAUGE
RIGHT, RIGHT.
THAT'S GREAT.
I TELL MIKE THERE ARE
NO SURVIVING POLICE RECORDS
OF ANY OTHER SHOTGUN
BEING RECOVERED BY POLICE
AND TIED TO THE KILLINGS.
WHILE WE CAN'T CONCLUSIVELY LINK
YOUR GUN TO THE MASSACRE,
NO EVIDENCE RULES IT OUT.
VERY INTERESTING.
SO IF THE ORIGINAL SHELLS
SURFACE,
THEN WE WOULD BE ABLE
TO FINISH GODDARD'S WORK
AND DETERMINE IF YOUR GUN
FIRED THEM.
HOW DO YOU THINK
YOUR FATHER WOULD FEEL,
THE FACT THAT WE'VE COME
THIS FAR?
HE WOULD BE ECSTATIC.
HE WOULD SAY,
"I TOLD YOU SO."
THANK YOU, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
FRED BURKE WAS NEVER CONVICTED
FOR THE MASSACRE.
INSTEAD, HE WAS PUT AWAY
FOR KILLING POLICE OFFICER
CHARLES SKELLY.
CAPONE WAS EVENTUALLY BROUGHT
DOWN ON CHARGES OF TAX EVASION.
BUT GODDARD'S WORK
BROUGHT CREDIBILITY
TO THE YOUNG FIELD
OF BALLISTICS.
HE WAS GIVEN RESOURCES
TO OPEN
ONE OF THE NATION'S FIRST
INDEPENDENT CRIME LABS
AND CONTINUED TO PIONEER
TECHNIQUES
THAT ARE STILL USED TODAY.
FOR MORE OF MY INTERVIEW
WITH ART BELIK,
VISIT HISTORY DETECTIVES
ON THE WEB AT pbs.org.
THE GUN THAT MADE
THE '20s ROAR
WAS INSPIRED BY WORLD WAR I
TRENCH WARFARE.
THE THOMPSON SUBMACHINE GUN
WAS DESIGNED
BY RETIRED GENERAL
JOHN THOMPSON.
EARLY MACHINE GUNS
WERE EXTREMELY HEAVY
AND TOOK SEVERAL MEN
TO OPERATE.
THOMPSON'S SOLUTION WAS
A RAPID-FIRING WEAPON
OPERATED BY
A SINGLE SOLDIER.
THE "TRENCH BROOM"
WAS DESIGNED
TO SWEEP THE ENEMY
OUT OF FOXHOLES.
BUT THE GUN WASN'T READY
UNTIL AFTER THE WAR ENDED,
SO THE GENERAL TRIED SELLING IT
TO THE AMERICAN PUBLIC.
ONE NOTORIOUS AD FEATURED
A COWBOY DEFENDING HIS RANCH
FROM BANDITS.
DEEMED SIMPLE, SAFE, STURDY,
AND SURE IN ACTION,
AN ORIGINAL TOMMY COULD FIRE
1,500 ROUNDS PER MINUTE.
GANGSTERS SAW THE POTENTIAL.
THE GUN WAS SUCH A FAVORITE
OF THE CHICAGO MOB
THAT IT WAS ALSO KNOWN
AS THE CHICAGO TYPEWRITER,
THE CHICAGO PIANO,
AND THE CHICAGO ORGAN GRINDER.
FOR CONCEALMENT, THE COMPACT GUN
COULD BE TOTED AROUND
IN A REFITTED
MUSICAL INSTRUMENT CASE.
THE THOMPSON DID MAKE IT
TO THE BATTLEFIELD
IN WORLD WAR II.
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS
WERE ORDERED
AT A COST OF NEARLY
$130 MILLION TOTAL.
BY THE END OF THE WAR,
LIGHTER AND CHEAPER COMPETITORS
ENDED THE TOMMY'S REIGN.
Tukufu:
OUR NEXT STORY INVESTIGATES
A DEATH THREAT SENT
TO ONE OF THE FIRST PRESIDENTS
OF THE UNITED STATES.
ON APRIL 14, 1865,
A MAN STANDING
IN THE SHADOWS
OF PRESIDENT ABRAHAM LINCOLN'S
THEATER BOX
FIRED ONE FINAL SHOT.
IT WAS THE FIRST ASSASSINATION
OF AN AMERICAN PRESIDENT,
AND JOHN WILKES BOOTH'S MOTIVES
HAVE BEEN QUESTIONED
AND STUDIED FOR GENERATIONS.
NOW, ALMOST 150 YEARS LATER,
MARSHA MULLIN
OF NASHVILLE, TENNESSEE,
HAS LEARNED OF A LETTER
SUPPOSEDLY WRITTEN
BY JOHN WILKES BOOTH'S FATHER
TO ANOTHER AMERICAN PRESIDENT.
TODAY SOMEBODY WOULD BE TAKEN
OFF TO JAIL IN FIVE MINUTES
FOR WRITING A LETTER
LIKE THAT.
MARSHA HAS INVITED ME
TO THE HERMITAGE,
PRESIDENT ANDREW JACKSON'S
FAMILY HOME IN NASHVILLE,
WHERE SHE IS CHIEF CURATOR.
SO WHAT DO YOU HAVE FOR ME?
WELL, A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO,
A VISITOR BROUGHT TO
OUR ATTENTION THIS LETTER,
WHICH WAS A DEATH THREAT
TO ANDREW JACKSON
WRITTEN IN 1835.
I REALLY DIDN'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT IT,
SO I GOT A COPY OF IT
FROM THE LIBRARY OF CONGRESS.
THE SIGNATURE ON
THE DEATH THREAT READS
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH.
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
WAS A VERY FAMOUS ACTOR,
BUT INTERESTINGLY ENOUGH,
HE WAS ALSO THE FATHER
OF JOHN WILKES BOOTH.
NOW, THAT'S AN INTERESTING
CONNECTION.
IT'S VERY INTERESTING.
IT'S DATED
THE 4th OF JULY, 1835,
FROM BROWER'S HOTEL,
PHILADELPHIA.
"YOU DAMNED OLD SCOUNDREL,
I WILL CUT YOUR THROAT
WHILST YOU ARE SLEEPING."
HE'S INSISTING THAT JACKSON
PARDON TWO MEN ON DEATH ROW.
"I'LL HAVE YOU BURNT
AT THE STAKE
"IN THE CITY OF WASHINGTON.
YOUR MASTER,
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH."
MAN, NOW THIS IS A THREAT.
SO THE FATHER OF THE GUY
WHO KILLED LINCOLN
THREATENED TO ASSASSINATE
A PRESIDENT.
WELL, THAT'S THE QUESTION.
BECAUSE WHEN YOU LOOK
AT THE BACK OF THE LETTER,
SOMEONE HAS WRITTEN
"ANONYMOUS."
AND SO THAT WAS VERY CURIOUS.
IS IT BY JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
OR NOT?
JACKSON SCHOLARS
SEEM TO BELIEVE
THAT IT WAS WRITTEN
BY SOMEONE ELSE.
WE'D LIKE TO KNOW
IF JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
REALLY WROTE THIS LETTER,
AND IF HE DID, WHY?
WELL, LET ME SEE IF I CAN FIND
AN ANSWER TO YOUR QUESTION.
THE SINS OF A FATHER
ARE NOT NECESSARILY VISITED
UPON THE SON.
BUT PRESIDENT LINCOLN'S MURDER
ALTERED AMERICAN HISTORY.
IF JOHN WILKES BOOTH'S FATHER
ALSO THREATENED THE LIFE
OF A SITTING PRESIDENT,
THAT'S CERTAINLY INTERESTING
AND POSSIBLY SIGNIFICANT.
JACKSON WAS THE 7th PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES
AND FIRST TOOK OFFICE
IN 1829.
JUNIUS BOOTH WAS THE POPULAR
SHAKESPEAREAN ACTOR OF THE DAY.
THE QUESTION IS,
WHY HAVE HISTORIANS DOUBTED
THAT JUNIUS BOOTH WROTE THIS
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
MARSHA'S LEFT ME
20th-CENTURY PUBLICATIONS
OF A JACKSON BIOGRAPHY
AND A COLLECTION
OF HIS CORRESPONDENCE.
BOTH VOLUMES INCLUDE MENTION
OF OUR LETTER.
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH HERE
IS IN QUOTATION MARKS.
BOOTH, IN QUOTATION MARKS,
TO ANDREW JACKSON,
JULY 4, 1835.
THE QUOTATION MARKS INDICATE
THE AUTHORS AND EDITORS
ALSO DOUBTED THAT BOOTH WROTE
THE DEATH THREAT.
I NEED TO FOUND OUT
IF THESE DOUBTS
ARE BASED ON
SOME ACTUAL EVIDENCE.
THE LETTER WRITER,
WHOEVER HE WAS,
WANTED TWO MEN PARDONED:
DE RUIZ AND DE SOTO.
I WONDER WHAT OTHER CLUES
THERE MIGHT BE.
IT SAYS DOWN HERE
IN A POSTSCRIPT,
"YOU KNOW ME, LOOK OUT."
DOES IT MEAN THAT
HE KNEW HIM PERSONALLY?
DOES IT MEAN
THAT HE KNEW OF HIM?
"I WROTE TO YOU
REPEATED CAUTIONS."
DID HE WRITE MORE THREATS
TO THE PRESIDENT?
THE PAPERS OF ANDREW JACKSON
PROJECT
AT THE UNIVERSITY OF TENNESSEE
IN KNOXVILLE
IS IN THE PROCESS OF PUBLISHING
AN UPDATED VERSION
OF EVERY KNOWN DOCUMENT
THAT JACKSON WROTE OR RECEIVED.
DAN FELLER IS THE DIRECTOR
AND EDITOR OF THE PROJECT.
LET'S GO INTO
THE JACKSON PAPERS.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
THIS LETTER BEFORE?
OH, YES, WE KNOW IT WELL.
WE DON'T THINK THAT THE REAL
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH WROTE IT.
OUR ASSUMPTION IS THAT THE
ORIGINAL NOTATION WAS CORRECT,
THAT IT'S ANONYMOUS.
DAN EXPLAINS THAT
PRESIDENT JACKSON'S STRONG-HAND
AND OFTEN UNPOPULAR POLICIES
HAD MADE HIM A LIGHTNING ROD
FOR CRITICISM AND THREATS.
SIX MONTHS BEFORE
OUR LETTER WAS WRITTEN,
HE WAS THE VICTIM OF
THE FIRST ASSASSINATION ATTEMPT
AGAINST AN AMERICAN PRESIDENT.
A DERANGED HOUSE PAINTER
ATTEMPTED TO SHOOT HIM
OUTSIDE THE CAPITOL BUILDING,
BUT THE PISTOL MISFIRED.
SHORTLY AFTER THAT,
THE WASHINGTON GLOBE PUBLISHED
SEVERAL COLUMNS
OF ASSASSINATION LETTERS
THAT IT SAID JACKSON
HAD RECEIVED.
LET ME PUT THESE UP
ON OUR COMPUTER SCREEN
SO YOU CAN READ THEM BETTER.
HERE'S ONE.
"DAMN YOUR OLD SOUL,
"IF YOU DO NOT DO SOMETHING
FOR THE GOOD OF THE COUNTRY,
I WILL MURDER YOU."
WOW.
DAN SAYS JACKSON
DREW PUBLIC CRITICISM
BECAUSE HE WANTED TO DO AWAY
WITH THE FEDERALLY CHARTERED
BANK OF THE UNITED STATES,
WHICH HE REGARDED AS AN
UNCONSTITUTIONAL CONCENTRATION
OF FINANCIAL POWER.
HERE'S ANOTHER ONE:
"REMOVE THEM DEPOSITS BACK AGAIN
AND RECHARTER THE BANK,
"OR YOU WILL CERTAINLY BE SHOT
IN LESS THAN TWO WEEKS,
AND THAT BY MYSELF!"
THE UNITED STATES SENATE
ACTUALLY CENSURED JACKSON
FOR REMOVING THE DEPOSITS,
THE ONLY TIME A PRESIDENT
HAS EVER BEEN CENSURED
BY THE SENATE.
DAN SAYS T RUIZ AND DE SOTO
MENTIONED IN OUR LETTER
WERE SPANISH PIRATES OPERATING
OUT OF HAVANA.
WITH TEN OTHERS,
THEY HAD ROBBED
AN AMERICAN MERCHANT SHIP
IN SEPTEMBER 1832.
THE PIRATES' CAPTURE
AND SUBSEQUENT TRIAL
ELECTRIFIED THE NATION.
THIS WAS A HUGE CASE.
IT HAD ALL OF THE ASPECTS
OF A MODERN SHOW TRIAL.
ONE OF THE SPANIARDS,
DE SOTO,
WAS PARDONED MOST LIKELY
BECAUSE HE PREVIOUSLY HAD SAVED
THE LIVES OF SOME
AMERICAN SAILORS.
DAN SAYS THE PARDON
WAS ALMOST CERTAINLY NOT
AS A RESULT
OF THE DEATH THREAT.
HOW SERIOUSLY WAS
THIS THREAT TAKEN?
DAN DOUBTS THERE WAS
ANY OFFICIAL INVESTIGATION
INTO THE LETTER.
THE OFFICE OF THE PRESIDENT
DID NOT HAVE
THE PROTECTIVE LAYERS
IT HAS TODAY.
THERE WAS NO SECRET SERVICE,
THERE WAS NO FEDERAL BUREAU
OF INVESTIGATION,
THERE WERE REALLY
NO WHITE HOUSE POLICE.
IN FACT, ASSASSINATING
THE PRESIDENT
OR THREATENING TO DO SO
WAS NOT A FEDERAL CRIME.
HERE HE SAYS, "I WROTE TO YOU
REPEATED CAUTIONS."
DO YOU KNOW OF ANY
OTHER COMMUNICATIONS
BETWEEN BOOTH AND JACKSON?
IF THERE WERE ANY,
WE WOULD HAVE SEEN THEM.
WE KNOW OF ONE LETTER
FROM SOMEONE CALLING HIMSELF
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH TO JACKSON,
AND THIS IS IT.
AND THAT'S IT.
AND NOT ONLY NO LETTERS
FROM BOOTH OR TO BOOTH,
BUT NO MENTION OF BOOTH
IN JACKSON'S CORRESPONDENCE.
WHOEVER WANTED
THESE PIRATES PARDONED,
DAN'S CONVINCED
IT WASN'T BOOTH.
EVERY HISTORIAN
PREVIOUS TO US,
EVERY JACKSON BIOGRAPHER,
HAS ASSUMED THAT BOOTH
DIDN'T WRITE IT.
SOMEONE IN HIS OFFICE --
AND HE HAD A NUMBER OF CLERKS
WORKING FOR HIM --
PROBABLY WROTE THIS WORD
"ANONYMOUS."
JACKSON DID NOT WRITE IT.
IT DOESN'T APPEAR TO BE
JACKSON'S HANDWRITING, NO.
HAS THERE BEEN AN ANALYSIS
OF THE HANDWRITING
IN THIS LETTER?
AS FAR AS I KNOW, NO ONE HAS
EVER TAKEN IT TO THAT STEP
BECAUSE THEY THOUGHT
IT WAS UNNECESSARY.
THAT SEEMS A CURIOUS OMISSION.
THE FOLGER SHAKESPEARE LIBRARY
IN WASHINGTON, D.C.,
HAS SEVERAL JUNIUS BOOTH
LETTERS IN THEIR COLLECTION.
HEATHER WOLFE IS CURATOR
OF MANUSCRIPTS.
SHE'S MADE SPECIAL ARRANGEMENTS
WITH THE LIBRARY OF CONGRESS
TO OBTAIN THE ORIGINAL THREAT
TO JACKSON.
HEATHER, NICE TO MEET YOU.
SO THIS IS THE ORIGINAL LETTER.
I PICKED TWO OF OUR
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH LETTERS
FOR A HANDWRITING ANALYSIS.
I PICKED THESE TWO LETTERS
BECAUSE THEY WERE CLOSEST
IN DATE AND FORMAT
TO THE 1835 LETTER
TO GENERAL JACKSON.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME
HEATHER HAS SEEN
THE ORIGINAL LETTER
TO JACKSON,
AND A COUPLE OF ITEMS
STRIKE HER AS ODD.
HE SIGNS THE LETTER TO JACKSON
WITH HIS FULL NAME,
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH.
ALL OF THE LETTERS AT THE FOLGER
ARE SIGNED J.B. BOOTH,
AND THAT WAS HIS TYPICAL
SIGNATURE.
THE REST OF THE LETTER
LOOKS AS IF
IT COULD'VE FLOWED
FROM THE SAME PEN.
AND YOU SEE HERE, "I WROTE
TO YOU REPEATED CAUTIONS,"
AND SEE THE BOTTOM OF THAT C,
HOW IT LOOPS AROUND
DRAMATICALLY?
WELL, IN THIS LETTER HERE,
WE SEE THE WORD "CAMP"
WITH THAT SAME VERY DISTINCTIVE
MAJUSCULE C,
WHICH IS VERY UNIQUE
TO JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH.
ONE OF THE MOST DISTINCTIVE
ATTRIBUTES HE HAS
IS THE CROSSBAR
ON THE MINISCULE T's.
SO IF YOU LOOK AT THE WORD "THE"
IN THIS LETTER,
THE CROSSBAR GOES FULLY ACROSS
NOT JUST THE T
BUT ALSO THE H AND THE E.
IF BOOTH DIDN'T WRITE THIS
HIMSELF,
SHE SAYS THE FORGER WAS
AT THE TOP OF HIS CLASS.
HEATHER'S MADE
ANOTHER DISCOVERY.
THIS LETTER FROM 1834
MENTIONS THAT HE NEEDED
TO ESCAPE THE FARM
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS
AND GO TO PHILADELPHIA,
AND IT SAYS, "THEREFORE
I STROLLED TO PHILADELPHIA.
BROWER'S HOTEL IS NOW
ABOUT THE BEST IN THAT CITY."
SO HE HAS A HISTORY
OF FREQUENTING
THE BROWER'S HOTEL
IN PHILADELPHIA.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DID JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
WRITE THIS LETTER?
BASED ON HANDWRITING ANALYSIS
ALONE,
YES, IT IS A JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
LETTER.
BUT I'M NOT A BOOTH EXPERT,
SO I THINK THAT'S A QUESTION
FOR BOOTH SCHOLARS.
WE'D NEED TO FIND OUT MORE
ABOUT THE CONTEXT OF THE LETTER.
WHY DID A FAMOUS
SHAKESPEAREAN ACTOR
CARE ENOUGH ABOUT THE FATE
OF TWO SPANISH PIRATES
TO HAVE PENNED
A DEATH THREAT
TO THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES?
GENE SMITH HAS AGREED
TO MEET ME
AT THE FOLGER LIBRARY'S
ELIZABETHAN THEATER.
HE'S THE AUTHOR OF A BOOK
ON THE BOOTH FAMILY'S INFLUENCE
ON AMERICAN THEATER.
IN ADDITION TO BEING
A GREAT ACTOR,
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH WAS
A GREAT MADMAN ALL HIS LIFE.
THERE'S NO QUESTION
HE WAS INSANE.
GENE SAYS THAT THE WILD
AND ERRATIC BEHAVIOR ONSTAGE
LED BOOTH TO BE DUBBED
"THE MAD TRAGEDIAN."
HIS BOUTS OF LUNACY
COULD INTERRUPT A PRODUCTION.
HE WOULD RUN AWAY
FROM THE THEATER
AND BE FOUND WALKING NAKED
DOWN THE STREET.
BOOTH'S EXCESSIVE DRINKING
EXACERBATED HIS MADNESS.
THEATER MANAGERS
WOULD LOCK HIM UP
TO KEEP HIM
FROM GETTING DRUNK.
FREQUENTLY, HE WOULD ESCAPE
AND SIMPLY VANISH
FOR THREE OR FOUR DAYS.
DID HIS FITS OF MADNESS
LEAD HIM TO ACTS OF VIOLENCE?
YES, BUT ONLY
VERY OCCASIONALLY.
HE WAS CAPABLE IN
THE MIDDLE OF A PERFORMANCE
OF BECOMING SO INVOLVED
IN KILLING DESDEMONA AS OTHELLO
THAT WHEN THE MOMENT CAME
TO PRESS THE PILLOW
AGAINST DESDEMONA'S FACE,
PEOPLE WERE AFRAID HE WOULD
ACTUALLY MURDER THE ACTRESS.
WELL, THIS LETTER
IS A THREAT
TO ASSASSINATE
PRESIDENT ANDREW JACKSON.
COULD THAT VIOLENT BEHAVIOR
HAVE EXTENDED TO MURDER?
IT IS POSSIBLE.
HOWEVER, IT'S IMPORTANT
TO KNOW
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
HAD A REVERENCE FOR LIFE
THAT WAS EXTRAORDINARY.
GENERALLY, HE HURT NOBODY
BUT HIMSELF:
HIS KIDS WERE FORBIDDEN
TO SWAT A FLY,
HE WOULD NOT CUT DOWN
A TREE.
HIS DEATH THREAT,
IF BOOTH PENNED IT,
MAY HAVE BEEN A BOUT
OF ALCOHOLIC MADNESS,
HIS REVERENCE FOR LIFE
BIZARRELY PROVOKING HIM
TO THREATEN MURDER.
MY GUESS WOULD BE
THAT MR. BOOTH PROBABLY READ
THAT JACKSON WAS CONSIDERING
THE EXECUTION OF THESE TWO MEN
AND, IN ONE OF HIS FRENZIES,
THREATENED TO KILL HIM.
HE DOUBTS PRESIDENT JACKSON
TOOK IT SERIOUSLY.
INDEED, THE LETTER SAYS,
"YOU KNOW ME,"
AND HE DID KNOW HIM.
JACKSON AND BOOTH
WERE CLOSE PERSONAL FRIENDS.
I THINK JACKSON WOULD'VE
PROBABLY SAID,
"WELL, THAT'S BOOTH FOR YOU,"
AND JACKSON WOULD'VE
LAUGHED IT OFF.
GENE PAINTS A PICTURE
OF A TURBULENT
AND DEEPLY TROUBLED MAN
FREQUENTLY ABSENT
FROM HIS FAMILY.
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
WAS AWAY ON THE ROAD,
TROUPING AROUND AS AN ACTOR
FOR MUCH OF THE YEAR.
BUT GENE IS RELUCTANT
TO MAKE ANY CONNECTION
BETWEEN THE DEATH THREAT
JUNIUS BOOTH MAY HAVE MADE
TO PRESIDENT JACKSON
AND HIS SON'S MURDER OF
ABRAHAM LINCOLN 30 YEARS LATER.
I THINK IT'S
EXCEEDINGLY IMPROBABLE.
HIS KILLING OF ABRAHAM LINCOLN
WAS SO ALIEN
TO HIS FATHER'S REVERENCE
FOR LIFE
THAT THERE CANNOBE
ANY TRACEABLE PATH.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT TO MAKE
OF ALL OF THIS,
AND I STILL DON'T HAVE
ANY SOLID EVIDENCE
TO SUPPORT
THE HANDWRITING ANALYSIS.
[ cell phone rings ]
HEY, DAN, HOW YOU DOING?
IT'S DAN FELLER.
SEEMS OUR MEETING
PROMPTED HIM
TO DO SOME ADDITIONAL RESEARCH.
I TELL DAN ABOUT
THE HANDWRITING COMPARISON
AND WHAT ELSE I'VE LEARNED
ABOUT JUNIUS BOOTH.
IT'S BEEN SUGGESTED TO ME
THAT JACKSON AND BOOTH
WERE ACTUALLY FRIENDS
AND THAT THIS LETTER
WAS WRITTEN IN JEST.
I DOUBT THAT VERY MUCH.
WE HAVE HERE ALL
OF ANDREW JACKSON'S LETTERS
THAT ANYONE KNOWS ABOUT;
WE KNOW OF NO EVIDENCE
TO PUT JACKSON AND BOOTH
TOGETHER IN ANY WAY.
HIS TEAM HAS UNCOVERED SEVERAL
NEW PIECES OF INFORMATION.
OUR LETTER'S DATED JULY 4th.
HE'S BEEN ABLE TO FIGURE OUT
BOOTH'S WHEREABOUTS THAT DAY.
THESE ARE NEWSPAPER
ADVERTISEMENTS
SHOWING THAT BOOTH WAS
INDEED IN PHILADELPHIA
ON JULY 3rd AND 4th.
HE WAS SCHEDULED TO PLAY
OTHELLO ON THE 3rd
AT THE CHESTNUT STREET
THEATRE...
I SEE.
AND SCHEDULED TO PLAY
RICHARD III ON THE 4th.
THAT PUTS BOOTH
IN PHILADELPHIA
AT THE TIME THE LETTER
WAS WRITTEN.
AND HERE'S
THE REAL CLINCHER.
THIS IS ANOTHER LETTER THAT
BOOTH WROTE IN AUGUST OF 1835.
HE APOLOGIZES FOR "THE
UNGRATEFUL AND SHAMEFUL CONDUCT
"I HAVE EVINCED TOWARD
THE WORTHY MANAGERS
"OF THE CHESTNUT STREET THEATRE
ON A RECENT OCCASION,
FRIDAY, JULY 3rd,
AND SATURDAY THE 4th.
IN FACT, HE DID NOT PLAY
ON JULY 3rd AND 4th;
HE DIDN'T SHOW UP.
SO HE WAS THERE, AND MAYBE
IN ONE OF HIS FITS OF MADNESS,
DID NOT PERFORM.
EXACTLY.
BUT AS FOR THREATENING
TO ASSASSINATE THE PRESIDENT,
I STILL DON'T HAVE
A SMOKING GUN.
BUT LOOK FURTHER DOWN
IN THE LETTER.
THERE AT THE END,
JUNIUS BOOTH HIMSELF GIVES ME
MY FINAL PIECE
OF THE PUZZLE.
"MY INSANE BEHAVIOR..."
I THINK I FINALLY HAVE
AN ANSWER FOR MARSHA.
VERY INTERESTING
INVESTIGATION.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR THE OPPORTUNITY
TO GET INTO THE LIFE
OF JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH.
I TELL MARSHA
THAT THE HANDWRITING
OF THIS ASSASSINATION THREAT
MATCHED OTHER LETTERS
PENNED BY BOOTH.
THAT'S COOL;
I AM REALLY PLEASED.
BUT WHAT TIED
THE CIRCUMSTANTIAL EVIDENCE
TOGETHER WAS AN OPEN LETTER
FROM BOOTH
THAT SEEMED TO BE
AN ADMISSION OF GUILT.
HE SAYS, "MY INSANE BEHAVIOR
IN WRITING INSOLENT LETTERS
"TO MY BEST PATRONS AND TO
THE AUTHORITIES OF THIS COUNTRY
I CAN SCARCELY HOPE
WILL BE PARDONED."
"THE AUTHORITIES
OF THIS COUNTRY."
YOU THINK HE'S REFERRING TO
PRESIDENT ANDREW JACKSON HERE?
I'LL BET HE IS, BECAUSE
ONE SENTENCE FURTHER DOWN,
HE SAYS, "MAY GOD PRESERVE
GENERAL JACKSON
AND THIS HAPPY REPUBLIC."
DAN SAYS
OUR HANDWRITING ANALYSIS
AND HIS QUESTIONING
OF CONVENTIONAL WISDOM
HAVE CORRECTED
THE HISTORICAL RECORD.
PRESIDENT LINCOLN'S KILLER,
JOHN WILKES BOOTH,
WAS FATHERED BY A MAN
WHO ALSO THREATENED
TO MURDER A SITTING PRESIDENT.
WE HAD ASSUMED, AS THOSE
BEFORE US HAD ASSUMED,
THAT THE REAL BOOTH
DIDN'T WRITE THIS LETTER
ON THE BASIS OF THAT
ONE WORD, "ANONYMOUS."
IT TURNED OUT HE DID.
IT REMINDS US ALWAYS
TO CHECK OUR FACTS,
ALWAYS TO GO BACK
AND VERIFY,
EVEN WHEN WE THINK WE KNOW
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED.
THAT IS AMAZING.
I'M SHOCKED.
I MEAN, IT'S AN INTERESTING
COINCIDENCE
THAT HE WROTE SUCH A LETTER
AND THAT HIS SON ENDED UP
ASSASSINATING LINCOLN.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR THE OPPORTUNITY
TO INVESTIGATE THIS STORY.
THANK YOU.
WHOSE JOB IS IT
TO PROTECT THE PRESIDENT?
WELL, BEFORE
THE SECRET SERVICE,
IT WAS SOMETIMES THE ARMY,
SOMETIMES THE LOCAL POLICE.
BUT LOTS OF TIMES,
IT WAS NO ONE.
JEFFERSON WALKED TO
HIS OWN INAUGURATION UNGUARDED.
MARTIN VAN BUREN WALKED
TO CHURCH ON SUNDAYS ALONE.
ON THE NIGHT LINCOLN
WAS ASSASSINATED,
A LOCAL WASHINGTON PATROLMAN
HAD BEEN ASSIGNED
TO PROTECT THE PRESIDENT,
BUT HE ABANDONED HIS POST TO
GET A BETTER VIEW OF THE PLAY.
THE SECRET SERVICE
WAS CREATED
FOUR MONTHS AFTER
LINCOLN'S ASSASSINATION
NOT TO PROTECT THE PRESIDENT
BUT TO PROTECT THE ECONOMY.
ITS AGENTS WERE CHARGED
WITH FIGHTING COUNTERFEITING.
TWO MORE PRESIDENTS
WOULD BE ASSASSINATED
BEFORE PRESIDENTIAL PROTECTION
BECAME A FULL-TIME
NATIONAL PRIORITY.
ONE GUNMAN KILLED
PRESIDENT GARFIELD
AT A WASHINGTON TRAIN STATION
IN 1881
AND ANOTHER GUNMAN SHOT
PRESIDENT McKINLEY
AT THE PAN-AM EXPO IN BUFFALO
IN 1901.
AFTER THREE ASSASSINATIONS
IN LESS THAN 40 YEARS,
CONGRESS FINALLY ASSIGNED
THE SECRET SERVICE
THE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THE SAFETY OF THE PRESIDENT
AT ALL TIMES.
Wes:
OUR LAST STORY EXPLORES
A BLACK MARKET TRADE
THAT SCANDALIZED
POST-CIVIL-WAR OHIO.
SINCE BEFORE THE TIME
OF THE PHARAOHS,
CIVILIZATIONS HAVE BEEN
BURYING THEIR DEAD
ALONG WITH PERSONAL EFFECTS,
JEWELRY AND ARTIFACTS
THAT COULD
MAKE A THIEF RICH
OVERNIGHT.
BUT LEFT UNGUARDED,
THESE COFFINS AND TOMBS
FREQUENTLY BECAME THE TREASURE
CHESTS OF GRAVE ROBBERS.
OVER THE CENTURIES,
COUNTLESS SITES
HAVE BEEN DESECRATED,
LOOTED,
AND VALUABLE HISTORIC ARTIFACTS
LOST TO THE BLACK MARKET.
HENRY DORRUM
OF CHESANING, MICHIGAN,
BELIEVES HE'S FOUND
THE 19th-CENTURY ANSWER
TO THIS HISTORIC PROBLEM.
I'VE BEEN COLLECTING
FOR ABOUT 25 YEARS,
AND THIS IS THE MOST UNUSUAL
OBJECT I'VE EVER FOUND.
[ ♪♪♪ ]
I WANT TO GET A LOOK
AT WHAT KIND OF STRANGE GADGET
HENRY BOUGHT FOR HIMSELF.
WELL, WHAT'S IN THE BOX?
I DON'T KNOW.
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
AN EXPLOSIVE DEVICE.
IT'S A HEAVY LITTLE DEVIL.
OH, THAT IS HEAVY.
WHERE'D YOU GET THIS THING?
AT A FARM AUCTION
IN SAGINAW COUNTY, MICHIGAN.
I LIKE UNUSUAL ITEMS
OF ALL KINDS.
I'M A COLLECTOR OF ANYTHING.
I'VE GOT TO ASK YOU,
ARE YOU SURE
THAT IT'S NOT GOING
TO EXPLODE?
OH, NO, IT'S BEEN
THOROUGHLY CHECKED.
I'VE HAD IT
FOR A LONG TIME,
AND YOU CAN LOOK DOWN
IN THERE,
AND IT'S COMPLETELY VOID
OF ANY POWDER.
HENRY EXPLAINS THAT ONCE
WHEN HE HAD IT ON DISPLAY
AT A BALTIMORE GUN SHOW,
A PASSERBY CLAIMED
HE RECOGNIZED THE DEVICE.
HE TOLD HENRY IT WAS
A KIND OF GRAVE ALARM.
I'D SEEN A PICTURE OF IT
IN A MAGAZINE YEARS AGO,
AND THAT'S WHAT IT WAS,
A GRAVE ALARM.
I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU, I'VE
NEVER HEARD OF SUCH A THING.
THE STRANGER TOLD HIM
GRAVE ALARMS WERE USED
TO PROTECT JEWELRY
AND OTHER VALUABLES
THAT MAY HAVE BEEN BURIED
WITH THE DECEASED.
THEY WOULD PUT ONE OF THESE
IN THE CASKET,
AND WHEN THE GRAVE ROBBER
OPENS THE COFFIN,
IT'S GOING TO BLOW UP
IN HIS FACE.
WHAT IS IT THAT YOU WANT ME
TO FIND OUT ABOUT THIS?
I WANT YOU GUYS TO FIND OUT
IF THIS TRULY IS A GRAVE ALARM.
WELL, HENRY, I'LL SEE
WHAT I CAN DIG UP.
I CAN'T FIND ANY MAKER'S MARK
OR SERIAL NUMBER,
WHICH IS A LITTLE ODD IF THIS
HAD BEEN MANUFACTURED FOR SALE.
I'M SKEPTICAL THIS IS AN ALARM,
AS HENRY BELIEVES.
IT LOOKS MORE LIKE SOME
KIND OF CIVIL-WAR-ERA WEAPON.
THIS IS A BOMB.
I MEAN, THIS THING WOULD'VE HELD
MAYBE HALF A POUND,
THREE-QUARTERS OF A POUND
OF BLACK POWDER IN HERE.
IT WEIGHS ABOUT EIGHT POUNDS
AND IT'S MADE OF CAST IRON,
WHICH WOULD'VE TURNED INTO
SHARDS OF DEADLY SHRAPNEL
IF THIS THING
HAD EVER EXPLODED.
THIS IS A SPRING-LOADED HAMMER
THAT WOULD'VE BEEN SET
BY MOVING THIS METAL BAR
ON THE COLLAR AROUND.
IF SOMEBODY STEPPED ON IT,
THIS FIRING MECHANISM
WOULD'VE ALMOST CERTAINLY
HAVE BEEN ACTIVATED.
SO WHEN THIS LITTLE COLLAR
IS MOVED
EVEN A FRACTION OF AN INCH,
THE HAMMER DROPS, AND THEN
IT HITS AN EXPLOSIVE CAP,
ALMOST LIKE A CAP GUN.
AND IF YOU LOOK, YOU'LL SEE THAT
THERE'S A HOLE ON THAT NIPPLE,
SO A SPARK WOULD TRAVEL
INTO THAT INTERIOR,
IGNITE THE GUNPOWDER,
AND BAM!
I'VE COME OUT
TO THE CORDOVA DRAGWAY PARK,
ABOUT TWO HOURS WEST
OF CHICAGO,
TO SEE JUST HOW DANGEROUS OUR
EXPLOSIVE DEVICE WOULD'VE BEEN.
LARRY LEFFERTS
OF CENTRAL STATES FIREWORKS
CONFIRMED THE AMOUNT
OF BLACK POWDER
OUR DEVICE WOULD'VE CARRIED.
WHAT WE DID WAS WE TOOK
THREE-QUARTERS OF A POUND
OF BLACK POWDER
AND WE BURIED THEM
AND PUT A LITTLE BIT
OF DIRT ON TOP
TO SIMULATE WHAT
IT MAY LOOK LIKE.
FIRE IN THE HOLE!
Wes:
WHOA, THAT THING COULD DO
SOME SERIOUS DAMAGE!
ABOUT AN HOUR FROM THE DRAGWAY
IS T ROCK ISLAND ARSENAL.
ESTABLISHED IN 1862,
IT'S THE NATION'S LARGEST
GOVERNMENT-OWNED
AND OPERATED ARSENAL.
KRIS LEINICKE IS
THE CURATOR OF THE MUSEUM,
WHICH HOUSES
AN EXTENSIVE COLLECTION
OF HISTORIC MILITARY WEAPONS.
THIS IS THE DEVICE
I WANTED TO SHOW YOU.
OKAY.
WOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
IT COULD BE?
IT LOOKS TO ME LIKE IT MIGHT
BE A CIVIL-WAR TORPEDO.
TORPEDO?
KRIS EXPLAINS THAT TODAY,
TORPEDO IS KNOWN
AS AN UNDERWATER WEAPON
LAUNCHED FROM A SUBMARINE
OR WARSHIP,
BUT IT ONCE HAD
A MUCH BROADER DEFINITION.
BEFORE THE FIRST WORLD WAR,
A TORPEDO MEANT ANY HIDDEN
EXPLOSIVE OR LAND MINE.
KRIS SAYS THAT PERCUSSION CAPS,
WHICH FIT OVER THE NIPPLES
AND PRODUCE THE SPARKS
THAT IGNITED THE GUNPOWDER,
WERE A CIVIL-WAR TECHNOLOGY.
SO IS THIS
A MILITARY DEVICE, THEN?
I DON'T THINK IT IS,
BECAUSE IT'S NOT MARKED,
AND A LOT OF MILITARY
EQUIPMENT AT THAT TIME
DID HAVE MARKINGS.
THE OTHER THING IS THAT
THE COLLAR ON THE NIPPLE
IS DIFFERENT THAN ON MILITARY
WEAPONS OF THAT TIME PERIOD.
LET ME SHOW YOU.
WE HAVE HERE
A CIVIL-WAR WEAPON
THAT WAS MADE
AT WATERTOWN ARSENAL,
AND YOU CAN SEE
THAT THIS ITEM THAT WE HAVE
HAS A SQRE COLLAR.
IT'S A TINY DETAIL, BUT KRIS
EXPLAINS THAT THE U.S. MILITARY
ROUTINELY USED SQUARE COLLARS
ON PERCUSSION WEAPONS.
OUR COLLAR IS RECTANGULAR.
I ASK KRIS IF SHE THINKS
THERE'S ANYTHING
TO WARREN'S IDEA
THAT THE DEVICE WAS DESIGNED
TO DETER GRAVE ROBBERS.
THAT'S REALLY INTERESTING, BUT
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF THAT BEFORE.
AND IF THIS HAD BEEN BURIED,
KRIS SPOTS WHAT APPEARS TO BE
A FATAL FLAW
IN THE DESIGN
OF OUR TORPEDO.
THE OTHER PROBLEM IS,
ONCE YOU BURIED IT,
YOU'D HAVE DIRT IN HERE,
AND THEN HOW WOULD THE HAMMER
HIT THE PERCUSSION CAP
THAT'S ON THE NIPPLE
TO CREATE THE EXPLOSION?
BUT IT'S DEFINITELY
PROFESSIONALLY MADE,
SO IT HAS TO HAVE SOME KIND
OF PRACTICAL USE.
YOU KNOW, IF OUR DEVICE
REALLY WAS MEANT
TO DETER GRAVE ROBBERS,
THERE'S GOTO BE SOME ACCOUNT
OF ONE OF THESE GOING OFF.
I TRY SEARCHING ONLINE
TO SEE WHAT I CAN FIND
ABOUT GRAVE ALARMS.
I DON'T TURN ANYTHING UP
SEARCHING UNDER GRAVE ALARMS,
BUT GRAVE TORPEDO,
WHICH IS THE TERM KRIS USED,
RETURNS A CURIOUS HIT.
OKAY, HERE'S AN ARTICLE
FROM THE RICHWOOD GAZETTE,
1881 IN OHIO:
"GRAVE ROBBER KILLED."
"THREE MEN WHO ATTEMPTED
TO ROB A GRAVE
"NEAR GANN,
IN KNOX COUNTY, OHIO,
"MET WITH A HORRIBLE OBSTACLE.
WHEN NEARING THE COFFIN,
THEY STRUCK A TORPEDO."
SO THESE THINGS
REALLY DID EXIST.
ONE OF THESE DEVICES,
PATENTED IN 1881,
SOUNDS SIMILAR
TO OURS.
THOMAS HOWELL
OF CIRCLEVILLE, OHIO,
PATENTED
AN EXPLODING SHELL
THAT WAS BURIED
RIGHT ABOVE A COFFIN.
AND IF ROBBERS TRIED
TO DIG UP THE COFFIN,
"THE SHELL WOULD EXPLODE,
INJURING OR KILLING
THE THIEVES."
IT APPEARS THAT IN THESE CASES,
AT LEAST, THE GRAVE ROBBERS
WEREN'T TRYING TO SWIPE JEWELRY
AND OTHER VALUABLES,
THEY WERE TRYING
TO STEAL BODIES.
IT SAYS THAT DURING THE 1800s,
MEDICAL SCHOOLS STOLE CADAVERS
TO DEMONSTRATE GROSS ANATOMY
TO THE STUDENTS
AND THAT THIS WAS PARTICULARLY
A PROBLEM IN OHIO.
SCOTT GAMPHER IS THE DIRECTOR
OF HISTORY COLLECTIONS
AT THE CINCINNATI MUSEUM CENTER
AT UNION TERMINAL.
HE'S NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE OUR DEVICE,
BUT HE UNDERSTANDS THE HISTORIC
NEED TO PREVENT BODY SNATCHING.
THERE WERE A LOT
OF DISSECTIONS
THAT WERE TAKING PLACE
IN THESE MEDICAL COLLEGES,
AND THUS A NEED
FOR A LOT OF CADAVERS.
BETWEEN 1865 AND 1890,
THE NUMBER OF MEDICAL SCHOOLS
IN THE U.S. ALMOST DOUBLED.
CINCINNATI-AREA MEDICAL SCHOOLS
COMPETED WITH EACH OTHER
TO OFFER PRACTICAL EXPERIENCE
TO STUDENTS.
BUT BODIES WERE NOT
EASY TO COME BY:
THE CHURCH OBJECTED,
AND MANY STATES
ONLY PERMITTED THE BODIES
OF EXECUTED CRIMINALS
TO BE USED FOR DISSECTION.
AND SO, REALLY, THE ONLY AVENUE
FOR THESE SCHOOLS
TO OBTAIN CADAVERS
WAS THROUGH THE BLACK MARKET.
IN OTHER WORDS, BY DOING
BUSINESS WITH GRAVE ROBBERS.
IN THE 1870s, PUBLIC CONCERN
ABOUT BODY SNATCHING
WAS AT A FEVER PITCH
IN OHIO IN PARTICULAR
BECAUSE OF
A NOTORIOUS INCIDENT.
THE BODY OF
JOHN SCOTT HARRISON,
FATHER OF FUTURE PRESIDENT
BENJAMINM A ROPE
DOWN A DARK SHAFT
AT THE MEDICAL COLLEGE OF OHIO,
PROVOKING ENORMOUS OUTRAGE.
IT WAS PARTICULARLY BAD
BECAUSE MEASURES HAD BEEN TAKEN
BY THE HARRISON FAMILY
TO PREVENT THIS VERY THING
FROM HAPPENING.
SCOTT SHOWS ME
AN ARTICLE
FROM THE CINCINNATI
DAILY COMMERCIAL
WRITTEN IN 1878 JUST AFTER
HARRISON'S BODY WAS STOLEN.
"IF CEMENTED WALLS CAREFULLY
AND SKILLFULLY CONSTRUCTED,
"AND VAST WEIGHTS, REQUIRING THE
STRENGTH OF MANY MEN TO LIFT,
"AND HIRED AND PRE-PAID WATCHMEN
"COULD NOT SAVE THEIR LOVED
AND HONORED PARENT'S GRAVE
FROM DESECRATION AND DISHONOR,
WHAT COULD?"
WOW.
AND I THINK THAT'S
ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT SHOCKED THE PUBLIC
SO MUCH:
"WELL, IF IT COULD HAPPEN
TO THE HARRISONS,
IT COULD HAPPEN
TO ANYBODY."
THE PUBLIC HAD
RUN OUT OF WAYS
TO SECURE
THEIR LOVED ONE'S GRAVE,
SO THEY TURNED TO DEADLY
EXPLOSIVES AS A LAST RESORT.
BUT IS OUR DEVICE REALLY
ONE OF THESE TORPEDOES?
WITHOUT A MAKER'S MARK
OR A CLEAR EXPLANATION
FOR HOW IT MIGHT'VE WORKED,
I'M STILL NOT SURE
WHAT WE HAVE.
SCOTT PUT ME IN CONTACT
WITH PAUL MAYBERRY,
THE LOCAL HISTORIAN
OF PICKAWAY COUNTY, OHIO.
PICKAWAY INCLUDES
THE TOWN OF CIRCLEVILLE,
WHERE THOMAS HOWELL
INVENTED HIS TORPEDO.
MY RESEARCH LED ME
TO CIRCLEVILLE
BECAUSE OF THIS OBJECT.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS?
WELL, THAT'S REALLY SOMETHING.
PAUL HAS NEVER SEEN
ONE OF THESE BEFORE,
BUT HE SAYS GRAVE TORPEDOES
HAVE A LONG HISTORY
IN THE REGION.
OUR LOCAL CEMETERY
ABOLISHED THE USE OF THEM,
I THINK, IN 1890 BECAUSE IT WAS
TOO MUCH OF A DANGER
TO THE PEOPLE WHO WERE
WORKING IN THE CEMETERY.
SUPPOSEDLY THERE WAS A GUY
NAMED THOMAS HOWELL
WHO LIVED HERE IN CIRCLEVILLE
WHO MADE DEVICES LIKE THIS.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF HOWELL?
YES, I HAVE.
I'VE DONE SOME RESEARCH
ON THOMAS HOWELL.
HE WAS A WATCH MAKER AND TIMES
GOT A LITTLE TOUGH FOR HIM,
AND HE DECIDED TO RESOLVE
SOME OF THE PROBLEMS
WE HAD WITH GRAVE ROBBING.
PAUL ASSEMBLED A NUMBER
OF LOCAL ARTICLES ON HOWELL
THAT HE COPIED
FROM OLD NEWSPAPERS.
THIS IS SOME OF THE ADVERTISING
THAT HE DID.
SO IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S FROM THE NEWSPAPER
FROM JULY 11, 1879.
THE AD SAYS,
"SLEEP WELL, SWEET ANGEL.
"LET NO FEARS OF GHOULS
DISTURB THY REST,
"FOR ABOVE THY SHROUDED FORM
LIES A TORPEDO,
"READY TO MAKE MINCE-MEAT
OF ANYONE
WHO ATTEMPTS TO CONVEY YOU
TO THE PICKLING VAT."
WOW, THAT IS INCREDIBLE!
I MEAN, THAT'S PRETTY GOOD
DIRECT MARKETING, ISN'T IT?
IT IS.
BUT THE PICTURE OF HOWELL'S
GRAVE TORPEDO
LOOKS NOTHING LIKE OURS.
DO WE HAVE
A GRAVE TORPEDO?
AND HOW WOULD IT HAVE WORKED?
HERE'S THE PROBLEM
THAT I HAVE.
IF YOU SET THIS THING
AND YOU PUT IT INTO A GRAVE,
WHAT'S TO PREVENT IT FROM
EXPLODING IN YOUR FACE?
WELL, THIS IS
AN INGENIOUS DEVICE.
WHAT PAUL SHOWS ME NEXT
GIVES ME THE ANSWER I NEED
FOR WARREN.
WHEN YOU FIRST SHOWED ME
THIS THING
AND YOU THOUGHT IT WAS
SOME SORT OF A GRAVE ALARM,
I SAID, "COME ON,
THIS GUY'S CRAZY!
IT COULDN'T BE
A GRAVE ALARM."
BUT AS I GOT INTO
THE INVESTIGATION,
I DISCOVERED THAT
THIS IS NOT SO MUCH AN ALARM
AS IT IS A DEADLY WEAPON.
OH, YEAH?
I TELL HENRY
THAT HIS DEVICE WAS DESIGNED
TO DETER THIEVES STEALING
BODIES, NOT VALUABLES.
WELL, THE GUYS I TALKED TO
WERE HALF RIGHT, ANYWAY.
HERE'S THE THING
I COULDN'T FIGURE OUT:
HOW COULD YOU PUT THIS
INTO A GRAVE,
SET THE TRIGGERS,
AND FILL THE GRAVE UP
WITHOUT BLOWING
YOUR HEAD OFF?
YOU GOT ME IN SUSPENSE HERE!
THOMAS HOWELL WAS SO SUCCESSFUL
WITH HIS FIRST GRAVE TORPEDO
THAT HE DESIGNED
ANOTHER ONE,
AND I HAVE A PATENT
FOR THAT ONE HERE.
NO, REALLY?
"GRAVE TORPEDO,
DECEMBER 20, 1881."
THE OLD PATENT PAPERS
SHOW A CURIOUS PARABOLA,
OR ARC, OVER THE TOP
OF OUR TORPEDO,
AND SUDDENLY I UNDERSTAND HOW
OUR DEVICE IS SUPPOSED TO WORK.
WHAT'S MISSING FROM HERE
IS A THIN METAL SHIELD
THAT FIT OVER THIS
THAT HAD A HOLE
IN THE MIDDLE...
RIGHT.
THAT ACCORDING TO THE PATENT
PAPERS, YOU'D TAKE A LONG TUBE,
LIKE A STANDPIPE, YOU'D
PUT A FUNNEL UP AT THE TOP,
AFTER THIS IS BURIED
IN THE GRAVE...
CORRECT.
AND YOU'D FILL THIS CHAMBER UP
WITH GUNPOWDER.
THEN ONCE THE CHAMBER'S
FILLED UP,
YOU'D DROP A CORK DOWN
THE STANDPIPE, OR SOME STOPPER.
WHEN THE TRIPWIRES SECURED
TO THE COLLAR
ARE DISTURBED
BY A GRAVE ROBBER...
THE THING GOES KA-BOOM!
WOW, I WOULD SAY
THAT'S THE SAME DEVICE.
BECAUSE HIS DEVICE
HAS NO MARKINGS ON IT
AND BECAUSE IT'S NOT
AN EXACT MATCH,
HENRY MAY HAVE A PROTOTYPE
OF HOWELL'S PATENTED
GRAVE TORPEDO.
IT'S SO CLOSE THAT
IT'S GOT TO BE IT.
IT'S GOT TO BE.
YOU GUYS REALLY
DID A JOB ON THIS.
THIS IS WORTH KNOWING.
THIS IS -- I MEAN,
THIS IS HISTORY.
WELL, THIS HAS BEEN
A GREAT INVESTIGATION,
AND I REALLY APPRECIATE YOU
BRINGING THIS TO ME.
YOU'RE RIGHT
ON THE BALL, WES.
PUT 'ER THERE, PAL.
IN 1881, THE YEAR HOWELL'S
GRAVE TORPEDO WAS PATENTED,
OHIO ENACTED
THE ANATOMY LAW.
IT PERMITTED MEDICAL SCHOOLS
TO USE UNCLAIMED BODIES
FROM PUBLIC INSTITUTIONS.
BY THE TURN OF THE CENTURY,
BODY SNATCHING CASES
HAD SIGNIFICANTLY DECLINED.
CADAVER STORAGE AND
PRESERVATION IMPROVED,
ALLOWING SCHOOLS
TO ACCUMULATE BODIES,
AND THE NEED FOR STEALING
FRESH HUMAN CORPSES
WAS A THING OF THE PAST.
EVEN PRESIDENTIAL BURIAL SITES
WERE PREY FOR GRAVE ROBBERS.
ELEVEN YEARS AFTER
ABRAHAM LINCOLN'S ASSASSINATION,
A CRIMINAL GANG HATCHED A PLOT
TO RANSOM HIS CORPSE.
THEY WANTED $200,000
AND THE RELEASE
OF AN IMPRISONED COHORT.
ON ELECTION NIGHT 1876, THE
THIEVES RAIDED LINCOLN'S TOMB
IN SPRINGFIELD, ILLINOIS.
BUT THE 500-POUND
CEDAR AND LEAD COFFIN
WAS TOO HEAVY TO MOVE.
TIPPED-OFF SECRET SERVICE AGENTS
ARRIVED IN TIME
TO CATCH THE WOULD-BE
GRAVE ROBBERS IN THE ACT.
AFTER THE ATTEMPTED ROBBERY,
THE NATIONAL LINCOLN
MONUMENT SOCIETY
SECRETLY MOVED LINCOLN'S CORPSE
TO ANOTHER PART OF THE TOMB.
FOR YEARS, THE PUBLIC PAID
THEIR RESPECTS
TO AN EMPTY SARCOPHAGUS.
BEFORE LINCOLN'S BODY WAS LAID
TO ITS FINAL RESTING PLACE,
IT WAS EXHUMED
AND CHECKED TWICE
TO MAKE SURE THE CORPSE
WAS STILL THERE.
AS A LAST SAFETY MEASURE,
IN 1901, PRESIDENT
AND MRS. LINCOLN'S BODIES
WERE ENCASED IN LEAD.
THEIR COFFINS WERE CAGED
IN STEEL
AND BURIED BENEATH
10 FEET OF CEMENT,
ENSURING THAT LINCOLN WOULD STAY
IN SPRINGFIELD FOREVER.
Tukufu:
BE A HISTORY DETECTIVE
YOURSELF.
HISTORY DETECTIVES WILL RETURN
IN A MOMENT, BUT FIRST...
GO TO pbs.org
AND LEARN MORE ABOUT
INVESTIGATIVE TECHNIQUES
OR SUBMIT YOUR OWN MYSTERY
TO THE TEAM.
YOU CAN ALSO FIND OUT MORE
ABOUT TONIGHT'S INVESTIGATIONS
ONLY AT pbs.org.
THIS EPISODE OF HISTORY
DETECTIVES IS AVAILABLE ON DVD.
THE COMPANION BOOK TO THE
PROGRAM IS ALSO AVAILABLE.
TO ORDER,
CALL PBS HOME VIDEO AT...
OR VISIT US ONLINE AT...
Captions by LNS Captioning
Portland, Oregon
www.LNScaptioning.com
Elvis Costello:
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ IT'S JUST LIKE
WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
Gwendolyn:
THIS PROGRAM WAS MADE POSSIBLE
BY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO YOUR PBS STATION
FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.