>> WE CAN TAKE THE STAMP OFF AND
LOOK HOW COOL THAT DESIGN LOOKS.
>> OH.
>> YOURS LOOKS AMAZING.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, YOURS IS ALL RIGHT.
AND THEN WE'LL TAKE THE SUSHI.
WE'LL JUST PLACE IT ON HOWEVER
YOU FEEL LIKE IT.
JUST REALLY PRETTY.
>> WATCH HER, MICHAEL.
WATCH HER.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE SURPRISED I CAN
USE THESE CHOPSTICKS, AREN'T
YOU?
>> I AM.
>> MM-HMM.
Y'ALL DON'T KNOW NOTHING ABOUT
THAT.
>> A LITTLE GINGER.
A LITTLE WASABI.
>> BAM.
>> YEAH.
>> SEE?
YOU TAKE THAT.
>> HAVE YOU EVER USED THIS ON
GUESTS AND NOT TOLD THEM?
KIND OF PULLING A MRS.
DOUBTFIRE?
>> BETWEEN US, YES.
ALL THE TIME.
>> LOOK AT THAT.
NOW COME ON.
THAT RIGHT THERE IS SOMETHING
SPECIAL.
>> IT IS SPECIAL.
>> AND IT ONLY TOOK THREE
SECONDS.
>> NOW WE WANT TO MOVE RIGHT
ALONG TO THE -- THIS IS THE LO
MEIN.
I'M GOING TO JUMP IN HERE.
BECAUSE WHEN I THROW DOWN, I
FOLLOW THROUGH.
LET'S DO THIS.
>> LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
>> LO MEIN IS GREAT TAKEOUT.
WHO DOESN'T LOVE CHINESE FOOD,
RIGHT?
>> WHAT IF YOU DON'T HAVE A BIG
FORK AT HOME?
>> JUST USE A MINI FORK OR A
REGULAR FORK.
WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO IS TWIRL
THE -- I'M GOING TO USE A
CARVING FORK, AND YOU CAN USE
THAT.
I'LL TWIRL THE NOODLES AROUND
THE FORK.
>> YOU MAY WANT TO GET TO THE
BIG FORK.
>> I'M TRYING TO WORK WITH TOOLS
I ALREADY HAVE AT HOME.
>> WE'RE GOING TO PUT IT IN THE
CENTER OF THE PLATE.
IT'S OKAY.
>> SARA'S DOING HERS IN PORTION
CONTROL.
>> BECAUSE IF YOU HAVE EATEN AT
A NICE RESTAURANT, THEY GIVE YOU
A BITE ANYWAY.
THAT'S A FIVE-STAR RESTAURANT.
>> I'M GOING TO TAKE THE
TWEEZERS AND THEN TAKE A LITTLE
BIT OF THE VEGETABLES.
>> AND I GOT TO SAY THIS.
IF I'M COMING OVER TO YOUR HOUSE
AS A GUEST, DON'T GO UPSTAIRS
IN THE BATHROOM,
AND GET THE TWEEZERS YOU HAVE
BEEN DOING YOUR EYEBROWS WITH
AND BRING THEM TO THE KITCHEN.
>> YOU WANT CLEAN TWEEZERS.
>> THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> YOU WANT A FRESH PAIR AT
LEAST.
>> EXACTLY.
SO WE'LL DO THAT.
WE'LL TAKE A LITTLE BIT OF THE
VEGETABLES AND KIND OF PLACE IT
AROUND.
>> I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU.
IF I SHOWED UP AT YOUR HOUSE,
I'M HAPPY.
IF I GET OVER TO YOUR HOUSE, I
AM FRUSTRATED.
>> IF YOU GO TO HER HOUSE,
YOU'RE HUNGRY.
>> FRUSTRATED, BUT SUPER SKINNY.
SO YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> SARA, PUT YOUR FINGER OVER
THE TOP BEFORE YOU SHAKE IT UP.
>> OKAY.
HAVEN'T GOTTEN TO THAT PART.
OKAY.
>> WE'RE USING A SQUEEZE BOTTLE.
THIS IS TERIYAKI SAUCE BECAUSE
IT TASTES GOOD WITH THE NOODLES,
BUT YOU CAN USE DUCK SAUCE OR
WHATEVER YOU WANT, AND I'LL DO A
SWIRLY DESIGN AROUND THE PLATE.
AND YOU CAN USE -- YOU CAN DO
WHATEVER DESIGN YOU WANT BECAUSE
IT'S ALL ABOUT CREATIVITY.
THERE IS NO RIGHT OR WRONG HERE.
YOU CAN DO A LITTLE BIT BETTER,
BUT IT'S ALL GOOD.
>> DON'T TELL SARA NO RIGHT OR
WRONG.
THAT'S WRONG.
>> AND YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE YOU
GET RID OF THOSE BOXES AND NOT
IN YOUR OWN TRASH.
YOU PUT THEM IN A TRUNK OR YOU
BURY THEM IN THE NEIGHBOR'S
YARD.
YOU DON'T WANT A TRAIL.
THEY WILL FIND YOU.
>> AND ANOTHER THING, YOU HAVE
TO MAKE SURE YOU LEAVE DIRTY
DISHES IN THE KITCHEN TOO.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> THEY THINK YOU COOKED IT.
>> WE PUT A LOT OF EFFORT INTO
OUR FAKING.
>> THIS IS THE FUN PART.
DESSERT IS MY FAVORITE.
I HAVE GOT A TOTAL SWEET TOOTH.
WE BOUGHT STORE-BOUGHT
CHEESECAKE, AND YOU CAN USE,
LIKE, PIES OR COOKIES OR
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
ABSOLUTELY.
>> OKAY.
>> SO I'M GOING TO TAKE THIS
LIGHTER.
WE HAVE SOME CHOCOLATE BARS.
YOU MIGHT HAVE SOME LAYING
AROUND THE HOUSE, AND I'M JUST
GOING TO LIGHT IT.
>> OH, THIS LOOKS COOL.
>> THAT MELTS THE CORNER, RIGHT?
>> OH.
>> WE'RE GOING TO TAKE IT AND
WE'RE JUST GOING TO STAMP IT
DOWN LIKE THIS.
>> OKAY.
>> CAN I TRY THAT?
>> YEAH, AND THERE YOU GO.
SO YOU TRY.
>> I WANT TO TRY.
>> YOU CAN DO THEM IN LITTLE,
LIKE -- YOU'RE NEXT.
YOU WANT TO USE TWO HANDS.
>> I WANT TO USE TWO HANDS?
>> TWO HANDS AND PRESS IT DOWN.
>> IT'S, LIKE,
TICK-TACK-TOE-ISH.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> WELL, THAT'S ACTUALLY GOOD.
>> THAT LOOKS LIKE YOUR TEETH,
MICHAEL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THAT WAS GREAT.
>> TO FINISH IT UP, YOU TAKE
YOUR CAKE.
YOU PUT IT RIGHT BETWEEN THE
GAP.
THAT'S RIGHT.
MARIA, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
WE'RE GOING TO USE THAT STUFF AT
HOME, AND YOU CAN MAKE SURE YOU
CHECK OUT MARIA'S
INSTAGRAM @THEARTOFPLATING.
COMING UP, WE HAVE THE
BACKSTREET BOYS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪♪
Cleaning floors with a mop and
bucket is a hassle,
meaning you probably don't
clean as often as you'd like.
For a quick and convenient
clean, try Swiffer WetJet.
There's no heavy bucket,
or mop to wring out,
because the
Absorb and Lock technology
traps dirt and liquid
inside the pad.
It's safe to use
on all finished surfaces
tile, laminate and hardwood.
And it prevents streaks and
hazing better than a micro fiber
strip mop, giving you a thorough
clean the first time.
For a convenient clean,
try Swiffer WetJet
with a money back guarantee.
Brand Power.
Helping you buy better.
I've just met this,
this incredible woman.
It's quite new so I don't
want to come in too hot.
Sophisticated.
Whoa...yeah.
I mean, in a good way.
What's her name?
Daisy.
Now in 6 bold flavors.
Ready for a lash lift?
L'Oréal's new Unlimited Lash
Lift Mascara.
1. Stretch it.
2. Tilt it.
3. Lift it.
Reach even smaller lashes.
Unlimited length.
Unlimited lift.
New Unlimited Mascara by L'Oréal
Paris.
♪
Try new Nature Valley
Fruit & Nut Granola.
A migraine hope
To be there...
for the good.
And not so good.
For the mundane.
The awe-inspiring.
The heart racing.
The heart breaking.
That's what life is all about...
showing up.
Unless migraine steals your
chance  to say "I am here."
That's why, we created Aimovig..
A preventive treatment for
migraine in adults.
One dose, once a month.
Aimovig is proven to reduce
the number  of
monthly migraine days.
For some, that number can
be cut in half or more.
The most common side effects
are pain, redness,
or swelling at the injection
site and constipation.
These are your days
What will each one bring?
Doesn't matter,
as long as you can say...
"I am here."
Talk to your doctor about
preventing migraine
with Aimovig.
And be there more.
Now, eyeliner goes NYC-proof.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil
from Maybelline New York.
Smudge resistant.
Sweat resistant.
Waterproof.
Up to 36-hour wear.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil.
Only from Maybelline New York.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> ALL I'M GOING TO SAY IS
EVERYONE HOLD ONTO YOUR INNER
FAN GIRL.
OUR NEXT GUESTS ARE ONE OF THE
BIGGEST BOY BANDS IN HISTORY.
THEY SOLD MORE THAN 130 MILLION
RECORDS WORLDWIDE.
THEY WERE JUST NOMINATED FOR A
GRAMMY.
>> OH YEAH.
>> AND THEIR TENTH STUDIO
ALBUM "DNA" IS OUT NOW.
PLEASE GIVE IT UP FOR HOWIE,
A.J., BRYAN, NICK AND KEVIN,
BETTER KNOWN AS THE BACKSTREET
BOYS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> CAN'T GET ENOUGH OF YOU GUYS.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN TOGETHER
FOR TWO DECADES.
YOU SOLD ALL THOSE ALBUMS, BUT
YOU'RE FAMILY MEN NOW.
YOU'RE MARRIED.
YOU HAVE KIDS.
YOUR RESIDENCY IN VEGAS HAS BEEN
AMAZING.
NOW YOU HAVE THE "DNA" TOUR
COMING UP.
YOU GUYS DON'T STOP.
>> YES.
WE HIT THE ROAD IN MAY.
WE START IN PORTUGAL.
>> PORTUGAL.
>> PORTUGAL, AND WE'RE GOING TO
BRING OUR FAMILIES WITH US AS
MUCH AS HUMANLY POSSIBLE.
>> SO YOUR FAMILIES WILL TRAVEL
WITH YOU AT SOME POINT?
>> OH YEAH.
>> WHEN THEY ARE NOT IN SCHOOL.
WHEN THEY ARE NOT IN THEIR
SPORTS AND STUFF, THEY COME OUT
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.
>> YOU AREN'T JUST BIG HERE.
YOU GUYS ARE GLOBAL,
INTERNATIONAL, IN FACT, YOU EVEN
DID SONGS IN OTHER LANGUAGES.
"I'LL NEVER BREAK YOUR HEART" IN
SPANISH.
>> SI.
>> AND "QUIT PLAYING GAMES WITH
MY HEART."
SO YOU REMEMBER ONE THING.
DO YOU REMEMBER ANY OF THE
LYRICS?
>> DO YOU WANT TO SING IT FOR
THEM?
>> LET'S DO SPANISH.
[ SINGING IN SPANISH ]
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THAT'S "I'LL NEVER BREAK YOUR
HEART" IN SPANISH.
>> WE KNOW SOME ITALIAN.
[ SINGING IN ITALIAN ]
♪
>> THAT'S "QUIT PLAYING GAMES
WITH MY HEART."
>> DO YOU KNOW THE LANGUAGE
WELL?
YOU KNOW IF YOU HAVE SOMEONE
THAT DOESN'T DO LANGUAGES WELL,
AND YOU'RE, LIKE, THAT'S NOT HOW
YOU SAY IT?
DID ANYONE STRUGGLE WITH THE
LANGUAGES?
>> OH YEAH.
>> SOMETIMES.
>> WE RECORDED -- I WAS GOING TO
SAY THIS.
THERE WAS A NEW SONG WE WERE
GOING TO RECORD IN SPANISH AND
I'LL NEVER FORGET.
IT WAS HARD.
IT WAS ON THE NEW RECORD
ACTUALLY A SONG IN JAPAN.
DIDN'T GET RELEASED HERE I DON'T
THINK, AND IT WAS REALLY
DIFFICULT, AND I JUST REMEMBER
THEM BEING, LIKE, SHAKING THEIR
HEADS IN THE BOOTH.
IT WAS ACTUALLY HARD FOR ME.
>> SOMETIMES WE CAN'T SPEAK
ENGLISH.
>> IT WAS HARD FOR ME AND I'M
HALF PUERTO RICAN.
IT WAS HARD FOR ME.
>> I ALSO HEARD THE SONG "I WANT
IT THAT WAY," WHICH IS ONE OF
YOUR BIGGEST HITS.
>> OH YEAH.
>> YOU GUYS -- THE PRODUCERS
WANTED TO YOU RECORD IT -- OR
CHANGE THE LYRICS BECAUSE IT
WOULD MAKE MORE SENSE?
>> THE LABEL.
THE WRITER AND PRODUCER LOVED IT
AND WE LOVED IT AND THEN THE
LABEL HEARD IT AND THEY WERE,
LIKE, THIS -- WE DON'T
UNDERSTAND THE SONG.
SO WE RE-WROTE THE LYRICS.
WHERE THE SONG ACTUALLY TOLD A
STORY, TOLD A NARRATIVE AND MADE
SENSE, BUT IT JUST DIDN'T SOUND
AS GOOD.
SO WE WENT BACK TO THE ORIGINAL
VERSION.
>> IT MAKES NO SENSE AND
EVERYONE LOVES IT.
>> IT BASICALLY WENT TO --
♪ NO GOOD-BYES, NO MORE LIES ♪
♪ I LOVE IT WHEN I HEAR YOU SAY
I WANT IT THAT WAY ♪
>> NO ONE NEEDS TO KNOW WHAT
THAT WAY IS.
>> IT'S AN OPEN INTERPRETATION.
>> JUST LIKE MEATLOAF.
I WOULD DO ANYTHING.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
LET THEM THINK.
IT'S SUPER PHILOSOPHICAL.
♪ I WON'T DO THAT ♪
>> TELL ME WHAT THAT IS.
TELL ME WHAT'S THAT.
>> THERE IS THAT ONE THING.
>> THE ONE THING.
>> HE WON'T RIDE A MOTORCYCLE.
>> KEEPS YOU GUESSING.
>> WE WERE SAYING YOU WERE
CLOSING UP YOUR RESIDENCY IN LAS
VEGAS, BUT YOU GUYS ARE GOING ON
TOUR.
>> YES.
>> TELL US ABOUT THE NEW TOUR.
>> I MEAN, WELL FIRST, I MEAN,
WE HAVE HAD THE MOST INCREDIBLE
TIME IN VEGAS WITH OUR
RESIDENCY.
IT LASTED A LOT LONGER THAN WE
EVER EXPECTED.
IT'S GONE TWO YEARS.
FEBRUARY AND APRIL ARE OUR LAST
RUNS, AND I ACTUALLY MOVED THERE
AND SO I'M RAISING MY FAMILY IN
LAS VEGAS, AND THAT'S -- IT'S
BEEN INCREDIBLE FOR US.
IT'S GIVEN US AN OPPORTUNITY TO
BE THE BEST BACKSTREET BOYS WE
CAN BE, AND PEOPLE COME FOR
BACHELORETTE PARTIES AND IT'S
INCREDIBLE, BUT NOW WE'RE
GETTING READY TO GO ON TOUR.
>> BRAND-NEW SHOW KICKS OFF IN
MAY IN PORTUGAL, GOES THROUGHOUT
EUROPE AND WE COME TO THE U.S.
AND CANADA.
ALL NORTH AMERICA, AND THEN IN
THE SUMMERTIME, AND FROM THERE,
WE'LL PROBABLY TAKE IT TO JAPAN,
SOUTHEAST ASIA, AUSTRALIA, SOUTH
AMERICA, AND THEN MAYBE -- YEAH.
>> SO SARA AND I, WHEN WE HAVE
OUR FREE TIME, WE LIKE TO SIT
AROUND AND WATCH YOUR VIDEOS.
WE DO.
>> THEY'RE GOOD.
>> WE WERE WATCHING THE
VIDEO "CHANCES."
WE REALIZED ONE THING.
YOU GUYS HAVE MASTERED THE
BROODING WALK.
>> YOU HAVE A MOVE.
YEP.
HERE IT GOES.
>> THE POWER WALK.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT'S FUNNY, THAT
PARTICULAR SHOT WAS NOT
ORIGINALLY SUPPOSED TO BE IN THE
VIDEO.
>> TRUE.
>> AND I ACTUALLY -- THIS IS MY
FIRST TIME STEPPING BEHIND THE
CAMERA.
I ACTUALLY CO-DIRECTED THIS
VIDEO.
>> OH, THAT'S AWESOME.
>> AWESOME.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WE WANTED TO HAVE THAT
PATENTED "I WANT IT THAT WAY"
BACKSTREET BOYS, WALKING AS A
GROUP LOOK.
>> WHOSE IDEA WAS THAT?
>> IT WAS KEVIN'S.
>> IT WAS.
IT WAS.
THERE IS SOMETHING TO BE SAID
ABOUT THAT POWERFUL --
>> BOY BAND WALK?
>> BOY BAND WALK.
>> THE CAMERA'S GOT TO BE DOWN
HERE, RIGHT?
>> ARE YOU WALKING AT REGULAR
PACE?
>> THAT'S WHAT I HAVE TO SAY.
A LOT OF TIMES THEY SPEED UP THE
MUSIC AND WE HAVE TO WALK EXTRA
FAST AND THEN THEY SLOW IT DOWN
AND IT LOOKS EPIC.
>> AS YOU SAID, THIS IS A
PATENTED WALK.
WE DID A ROUNDUP OF WHERE WE
MIGHT HAVE SEEN THIS BEFORE.
>> THERE YOU GO.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> DANG.
>> OH!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WE HAVE DONE A LOT OF WALKING
IN OUR CAREER.
>> OBVIOUSLY, IF WE EVER STOP
DANCING, WALKING, WE HAVE
NAILED.
>> WE HAVE WALKED THE WHOLE
PLANET.
>> WHEN WE NEED HIP
REPLACEMENTS, WE'LL JUST --
>> A FUN THING ABOUT SHOOTING
THOSE WALKS IS WHAT NICK WAS
SAYING.
THEY ACTUALLY SPEED UP THE
MUSIC, OKAY?
SO YOU'RE WALKING SO IT LOOKS
LIKE YOU'RE WALKING IN SLOW
MOTION SO IT'S POWERFUL, BUT
YOU'RE SINGING IN TIME WITH THE
MUSIC.
SO IT'S ACTUALLY WHEN YOU ARE
WALKING INSTEAD OF, LIKE --
♪ WHAT ARE THE CHANCES ♪
IT'S NOT IN REALTIME.
>> DO IT.
>> IT'S, LIKE --
♪ WHAT ARE THE CHANCES ♪
>> IT IS TRUE.
>> YOU FEEL KIND OF LIKE A
CHIPMUNK, BUT IT'S FUNNY.
>> I'LL NEVER LOOK AT THAT WALK
THE SAME AGAIN.
>> YOU HAVE TO KEEP THAT POWER
FACE, YOU KNOW?
>> SINCE YOU GUYS ARE HERE, WE
HAPPEN TO HAVE A CAMERA THAT'S
DOWN LOW, AND -- CAN WE DO A
LITTLE POWER WALK?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU HAVE TO GET YOUR FACE
RIGHT TOO.
WHAT'S THE LOOK?
>> JUST THINK THIS.
EYES THAT STARE RIGHT THROUGH
YOU.
>> LOOK AT THE CAMERA?
>> YOU LOOK RIGHT DOWN THE
BARREL.
>> DOWN THE BARREL?
>> YOU HAVE TO LOOK HERE.
>> LOOK THERE.
OKAY.
LOOKING RIGHT THERE.
>> I CAN DO THAT.
>> OKAY.
COME ON.
HERE WE GO.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE
BACKSTREET BOYS ARE GOING TO
PERFORM FOR US.
THAT'S NEXT SO DON'T GO
ANYWHERE.
WE MASTERED IT.
WE GOT IT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪ IT'S TOO LATE ♪
Those arms, they'll be jelly
tomorrow.
It'll hurt to sit.
And laugh.
'Cause that workout, is working.
Feed it, with Special K
with iron, protein and
B vitamins.
Feed your progress.
Feed your power.
Feed your change.
At last, one red that works on
everyone.
New Made for All lip color from
Maybelline New York.
Tested on 50 skin tones.
Sensational on all.
New Made for All.
Only from Maybelline New York.
When I walked through a
snowstorm for a cigarette,
that's when I knew
I had to quit.
For real this time.
That's why I'm using Nicorette.
Only Nicorette Gum has patented
dual-coated technology
for great taste.
Plus intense
craving relief.
Every great why,
needs a great how.
This is nice.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is nice.
Mmmm how did you make the
dip so rich and creamy?
Oh, it's a Philadelphia-
-Family Recipe.
Can I see it?
No.
New Philadelphia Dips.
So good,
you'll take all the credit.
♪ I'M A BIG KID NOW ♪
♪ WENT FROM BABY BOTTLES TO
DRINKING FROM SIPPY CUPS ♪
♪ WENT FROM WEARING DIAPERS TO
ROCKING THESE FRESH PULL-UPS ♪
♪ WE'RE 50 MILLION STRONG ♪
♪ SO PUT ON YOUR PULL-UPS
AND HELP US SING THIS SONG ♪
People everywhere
are confusing Quilted Northern
for a Bouncy Castle.d Northern
for a Bouncy Castle.
They're both durable, flexible
and nice to have at parties.
But Quilted Northern
is not a Bouncy Castle.
It's just really nice
toilet paper.
Do I use a toothpaste that
whitens my teeth,
or one that's good for my teeth?
Now I don't have to choose.
From Crest 3D White, the
Whitening Therapy collection
with new Spearmint and
Peppermint Oil.
It gently whitens,
plus it has a fortifying formula
to protect your enamel.
Crest.
Healthy, beautiful smiles
for life.
(KATY)
I was thrilled to be able to go
with my friends to our annual
get-together, especially after
being diagnosed last year
with advanced non-small cell
lung cancer.
(AVO)
Another TRU story with KEYTRUDA.
(DR. KLOECKER)
I started Katy on KEYTRUDA and
chemotherapy and she's getting
results we rarely
saw five years ago.
(AVO)
In a clinical trial,
significantly more patients
lived longer and saw their
tumors shrink than
on chemotherapy alone.
(DR. KLOECKER)
It's changed my approach to
treating patients.
(AVO)
KEYTRUDA may be used with
certain chemotherapies as
your first treatment if you have
advanced nonsquamous, non-small
cell lung cancer and you do not
have an abnormal
"EGFR" or "ALK" gene.
KEYTRUDA helps your immune
system fight cancer,
but can also cause your immune
system to attack healthy
parts of your body. This can
happen during or after treatment
and may be severe
and lead to death.
See your doctor right away if
you have new or worse cough,
chest pain, shortness of breath,
diarrhea, severe stomach pain
or tenderness, nausea or
vomiting, rapid heartbeat,
increased hunger or thirst,
constipation, dizziness
or fainting, changes in
urine or eyesight,
muscle pain or
weakness, joint pain,
confusion or memory problems,
fever, rash,
itching, or flushing.
These are not all the
possible side effects.
Tell your doctor about all your
medical conditions,
including immune system
problems, if you've had
an organ transplant, had or plan
to have a stem cell transplant,
or have lung, breathing, or
liver problems.
(KATY VO)
Where I am now compared to a
year ago,
it's a story worth sharing.
(AVO)
Living longer is possible.
It's TRU.
KEYTRUDA, from Merck.
With more FDA-approved uses for
advanced lung cancer
than any other immunotherapy.
Mascara in a snap.
New Snapscara from
Maybelline New York.
Smooth, clump-free volume.
Pure pigment formula means...
it's on & off in a snap!
No raccoon eyes.
Smooth, clump-free volume.
New Snapscara!
Only from Maybelline New York.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> WELCOME BACK, EVERYBODY.
HERE TO PERFORM THEIR NEW HIT
SINGLE, "CHANCES," ONCE AGAIN,
GIVE IT UP FOR THE ONE AND ONLY
BACKSTREET BOYS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
♪ WHAT IF I'D NEVER RUN INTO
YOU ♪
♪ WHAT IF YOU NEVER SMILED AT
ME ♪
♪ AND WHAT IF I HADN'T NOTICED
YOU TOO ♪
♪ AND YOU NEVER SHOWED UP WHERE
I HAPPENED TO BE ♪
♪ WHAT'S A GIRL LIKE YOU DOING
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS ♪
♪ ON A QUIET NIGHT, WHAT ARE THE
ODDS ♪
♪ WHAT'S A GUY LIKE ME DOING IN
A PLACE LIKE THIS ♪
♪ I COULD HAVE JUST WALKED BY,
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT ♪
♪ WHAT ARE THE CHANCES THAT WE'D
END UP DANCING ♪
♪ LIKE TWO IN A MILLION, LIKE
ONCE IN A LIFE ♪
♪ THAT I COULD HAVE FOUND YOU,
PUT MY ARMS AROUND YOU ♪
♪ LIKE TWO IN A MILLION, LIKE
ONCE IN A LIFE ♪
♪ WHAT ARE THE CHANCES ♪
♪ WHAT IF I HADN'T ASKED YOU
YOUR NAME ♪
♪ AND TIME HADN'T STOPPED WHEN
YOU SAID IT TO ME ♪
♪ OF ALL THE PLANS I COULD HAVE
MADE ♪
♪ OF ALL THE NIGHTS THAT I
COULDN'T SLEEP ♪
♪ WHAT'S A GIRL LIKE YOU DOING
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS ♪
♪ IN A CROWDED ROOM, WHAT ARE
THE ODDS ♪
♪ WHAT'S A GUY LIKE ME DOING IN
A PLACE LIKE THIS ♪
♪ GETTING CLOSE TO YOU, BUT HERE
WE ARE ♪
♪ WHAT ARE THE CHANCES THAT WE'D
END UP DANCING ♪
♪ LIKE TWO IN A MILLION ♪
♪ LIKE ONCE IN A LIFE ♪
♪ THAT I COULD HAVE FOUND YOU,
PUT MY ARMS AROUND YOU ♪
♪ LIKE TWO IN A MILLION, LIKE
ONCE IN A LIFE ♪
♪ WHAT ARE THE CHANCES ♪
♪ IS IT LOVE, IS IT FATE ♪
♪ WHO I AM, WHO'S TO SAY? ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW EXACTLY WHAT IT
MEANS ♪
♪ IS IT LOVE, IS IT FATE ♪
♪ WHERE IT LEADS, WHO CAN SAY ♪
♪ MAYBE YOU AND I WERE MEANT TO
BE ♪
♪ WHAT, WHAT, WHAT ARE THE
CHANCES THAT WE'D END UP
DANCING ♪
♪ TWO IN A MILLION, ONCE IN A
LIFE ♪
♪ THAT I COULD HAVE FOUND YOU,
PUT MY ARMS AROUND YOU ♪
♪ TWO IN A MILLION, LIKE ONCE IN
A LIFE ♪
♪ WHAT ARE THE CHANCES, TWO IN A
MILLION, ONCE IN A LIFE ♪
♪ WHAT ARE THE CHANCES ♪
♪ TWO IN A MILLION, ONCE IN A
LIFE ♪
♪ WHAT IF I I'D NEVER RUN INTO
YOU, AND WHAT IF YOU NEVER
SMILED AT ME ♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Okay, I never thought I'd say
this,
but I found bladder leak
underwear
that's actually pretty.
Surprised?
It's called Always Discreet
Boutique.
It looks and fits like my
underwear.
I know what you're thinking.
How can something this pretty
protect?
Hidden inside is a super
absorbent core
that quickly turns liquid to gel
for incredible protection.
So I feel protected and pretty.
Always Discreet Boutique. New
Color. New Size.
(Alert chime)
Hiyeeeeeee!
Oh! We all just
got new smartphones
at Cricket!
(Alert chime)
Hiyeeeeeee!
!Holaaaaa!
OK, bye-eeeee!
All: Bye-eeeeee!
(Chime)
♪ ♪ ♪
THE THINGS THAT MATTER MOST
HAPPEN ONE MORNING
AND ONE CUP AT A TIME.
THE THINGS THAT MATTER MOST
When I created
Knorr Selects,
I looked for real
ingredients for real taste.
Absolutely no artificial
flavors or preservatives.
Knorr Selects
real ingredients for real taste.
(coughs)
Hi Susan!
Honey? I respect that.
But that cough looks
pretty bad...
try this NEW Robitussin Honey.
The real honey you love...
Plus the powerful cough
relief you need.
Mind if I root through
your trash?
New Robitussin Honey.
Because it's never just a cough.
Meet the new sculpted brow.
New Tattoo Brow Pomade
from Maybelline New York.
♪♪
For up to 24-hour
sculpted brows.
New Tattoo Brow Pomade.
Only from Maybelline New York.
Sorry...
Hey.
He just likes cute dogs.
And pretty ladies.
Or is this your
buddy's kid over there
and you're just
using him as bait?
I'm blaming my friend
entirely because...
Thank you. Thank you.
That was not your dog.
Now in 6 bold flavors.
♪ When you have nausea, ♪
♪ heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, ♪
♪ upset stomach, ♪
♪ diarrhea... ♪
Girl, Pepto ultra coating will
treat your stomach right.
♪Nausea, heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, upset stomach,♪
♪ diarrhea... ♪
Try Pepto with Ultra coating.
See a little blood
when you brush or floss?
You may have gum disease
and could be on a journey
to much worse.
Try parodontax toothpaste.
It's three times more effective
at removing plaque,
the main cause of bleeding gums.
Leave bleeding gums behind
with parodontax
toothpaste.
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
Leave bleeding gums behind
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.