THE ENTIRE REGION.
WE WILL SEE IT ALL.
THE SNOW, THE FREEZING RAIN,
THE SLEET AND THE FLOODING.
>> DANGER FROM ABOVE AHEAD.
GLASS RAINING ON BETHESDA
SIDEWALK.
ABC7 BACK WHERE WE WERE TWO
YEARS AGO.
AND A ROUSING CELEBRATION.
>> THE FIREFIGHTERS MAKING A
BLESSED DELIVERY TO ONE OF
THEIR OWN.
>> NOW, "ABC7 NEWS AT 6:00".
ON YOUR SIDE.
>> THE SCHOOL CLOSINGS ALREADY
COMING IN.
>> CHECK OUT THE TICKER BELOW
OR OPEN UP THE STORMWATCH7 APP
TO SEE IF YOUR SCHOOL IS ON
THE LIST OF THE CLOSURES.
BILL KELLY WITH THE LATEST ON
THE STORM.
>> TOMORROW MORNING AT 4:00 TO
7:00 IS WHEN THE SNOW WILL
START.
A LITTLE BIT EARLIER FOR YOU
FOLKS IN THE SOUTHWEST AREAS.
BUT GENERALLY 4:00 TO 7:00
A.M.
THEN IT SNOWS ALL MORNING LONG
THROUGH AT LEAST 12:00 NOON.
ONCE WE HIT 12:00 NOON TO 4:00
P.M., THE EARLY TO THE
MID-AFTERNOON.
IT WILL TURN TO A MIX.
WE COULD SEE RAIN/SNOW MIX.
IT WILL TRANSITION TO RAIN BUT
THE STUFF AT THE SURFACE IS
STILL FREEZING.
BUT THEN BY 4:00 TO 8:00 P.M.,
LATE AFTERNOON TOMORROW, IT
WILL TURN TO ALL RAIN.
IT WILL END BY THURSDAY
MORNING AND FOG IS AROUND.
THE OUTLYING COUNTIES THAT IS
GENERALLY THE ENTIRE AREA.
THERE ARE SOME FOLKS IN
SOUTHERN MARYLAND AND THE
NORTHERN NECK WHERE THERE IS A
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY.
JUST SLIGHTLY LESS TOTALS BUT
YOU WILL GET SNOW AS WELL.
STAY WITH THE STORMWATCH7
WEATHER TEAM THROUGH THE
EVENING AND THEN, OF COURSE,
TOMORROW MORNING WHEN "GOOD
MORNING WASHINGTON" IS GOING
TO GO ON EARLY.
4:00 IN THE MORNING.
TRACKING THAT SNOW.
FROM THE ON SET, ALL THE WAY
THROUGH.
WE'LL BE ON THE AIR ALL
AFTERNOON.
>> Jonathan: THANK YOU.
PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY, INDIAN
HEAD HIGHWAY ADDING TO THE
REPUTATION AS ONE OF THE
DEADLIEST ROADS IN THE REGION.
WALDORF MAN WAS KILL AND THREE
PEOPLE HURT IN MULTI-VEHICLE
CRASH MONDAY IN ACCOKEEK.
MORE THAN 60 PEOPLE DIED ON
THE HIGHWAY IN A DECADE.
THE FACT THAT PEOPLE TWO DRIVE
ON THE ROAD DAILY KNOW TOO
WELL.
>> LATE AT NIGHT, THE DRUNK
DRIVING.
PEOPLE ON THE CELL PHONES.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU CAN DO
ABOUT IT.
>> Jonathan: THE COUNTY
LEADERS SAY THERE IS NOT MUCH
MORE THEY CAN DO AND DRIVERS
SHOULD TAKE MORE
RESPONSIBILITY.
THEY ISSUED NEARLY 4,000
TICKETS THIS YEAR.
>> Michelle: ABC7 COVERING
D.C. WHERE A NEW AMBULANCE
POLICY COULD MEAN PEOPLE WHO
NEED EMERGENCY CARE DON'T
NECESSARILY GO TO THE
HOSPITAL.
SAM FORD REPORTS HOW THE FIRST
RESPONDERS WILL DECIDE WHO
GETS A RIDE AND WHO DOES NOT.
>> RIGHT NOW THE D.C. FIRE
E.M.S. HAS THE AMBULANCES TO
TRANSPORT TO HOSPITALS THOSE
WITH THE POTENTIALLY LIFE
THREATENING SITUATIONS.
A.M.R. IF THEY DON'T BELIEVE
IT'S LIFE THREATENING AND
BEGINNING MARCH 1, MAYBE
NOTHING.
THE SLOGAN "YOU CALL WE HAUL"
NO LONGER APPLIES.
PERHAPS YOU WILL CALL AND THEY
WILL SEND YOU A LYFT.
L-Y-F-T.
>> A LYFT VEHICLE TO TAKE THEM
FROM WHERE THEY HAVE CALLED
FROM TO THE CLINIC.
>> TO ONE OF THE 21 DESIGNATED
CLINICS AROUND THE CITY LIKE
UNITY CLINIC IN NORTHEAST.
>> ONCE THE PATIENT IS HERE.
I WILL ASSESS THE PATIENT.
IF THEY HAVE TO GO TO THE
HOSPITAL.
OR IF THEY CAN BE SEEN BY A
DOCTOR HERE?
>> WE ARE CHANGING SOME OF
THINKING WE HAVE DONE FOR
YEARS AND YEARS AND YEARS.
>> FIRE E.M.S. OFFICIALS TOLD
US BEGINNING MARCH 1, A CALL
TO 911 AND THEY WILL SEND A
FIRE TRUCK OR THE AMBULANCE
OUT TO ASSESS.
PERHAPS HAVE YOU TALK ON THE
PHONE WITH A 911 NURSE.
THEN TELL YOU THEY ARE NOT
TAKING YOU TO A HOSPITAL.
>> WE ARE ACTUALLY SENDING
TRAINED EMERGENCY MEDICAL
TECHNICIANS AND THE PARAMEDICS
TO EVALUATE YOU.
IF WE EVALUATE YOU AND DECIDE
THAT YOUR SYMPTOMS ARE BETTER
SERVED IN A CLINIC, THEN DON'T
YOU THINK THAT WE SHOULD TAKE
YOU TO A CLINIC VERSUS
OVERCROWDED EMERGENCY ROOM?
>> THE CHIEF SAYS IT WILL CUT
DOWN ON THE LONG WAIT TIME IN
THE EMERGENCY ROOM AND MAKE IT
EASIER FOR THE CITY TO HANDLE
THE 500 TO 600 EMERGENCY
MEDICAL CALLS A DAY.
70% OF WHICH HE SAYS ARE NOT
EMERGENCIES.
REPORTING FROM NORTHWEST
WASHINGTON, SAM FORD, NEWS
NEWS.
>> Jonathan: WEST VIRGINIA
TEACHERS WENT ON STRIKE TODAY
AND AFTER JUST HOURS ON THE
PICKETED LINE, THE STATE HOUSE
DELEGATES KILLED THE BILL THAT
PROMPTED THE STRIKE IN THE
FIRST PLACE.
DECISION THAT WENT OVER WELL
WITH THE CROWD.
WEATHER PERMITTING SCHOOL
COULD RESUME TOMORROW BUT THE
TEACHER UNIONS ARE MEETING
TONIGHT TO MAKE A DECISION.
TEACHERS UNIONS VIEWED THE
BILL AS THE RETRIBUTION FOR
THE NINE-DAY TEACHER STRIKE.
IT WOULD HAVE CREATED CHARTER
SCHOOL AND ALLOWED THE
EDUCATION SAVING ACCOUNTS FOR
THE PARENTS TO PAY FOR PRIVATE
SCHOOL.
>> Michelle: NEW DEVELOPMENT
IN A SECRET SCHOOL RECORDING
FIRST REPORTED BY THE "7 ON
YOUR SIDE" I-TEAM.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL FALLING A
CIVIL COMPLAINT AGAINST THE
TEACHER AND THETEACHER'S
AIDES.
THEY ARE ALL THREE ACCUSED OF
VERBALLY ASSAULTING STUDENTS
AT BERKELEY HEIGHTS ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL.
>> I WILL CERTAINLY NOT ALLOW
SOME OF THE MOST VULNERABLE
MEMBERS OF THE COMMUNITY TO BE
TREATED IN AN UNLAWFUL MANNER
BY PUBLIC EMPLOYEES WHO ARE
SUPPOSED TO TAKE CARE OF THEM.
>> Michelle: ALL THREE HAVE
SINCE RESIGNED FROM THE SCHOOL
DISTRICT.
EACH NOW FACES A $5,000 FINE.
AND THE POSSIBILITY OF NEVER
TEACHING IN THE STATE AGAIN.
>> Jonathan: IN AUGUST OF
2017, ABC7 OBTAIN VIDEO OF THE
GLASS CRACKING.
YOU CAN KIND OF HEAR IT.
THIS HAPPENED FOUR MORE TIMES
SINCE THEN AND ONLY ON 7, THE
MONTGOMERY COUNTY REPORTER
KEVIN LEWIS EXPLAINS HOW THE
CAUSE STILL REMAINS A BIG
MYSTERY.
>> Kevin:4500 EAST-WEST
HIGHWAY IS SLEEK.
BUT THE OFFICE BUILDING IS
SHEDDING THE GLASS WINDOWS.
>> I BECAME AWARE OF IT IN
2017.
>> Kevin: AMANDA DOCUMENTED
FIVE SEPARATE INCIDENTS
INCLUDING YESTERDAY WHEN THIS
GLASS PANE CRACKED TO HUNDREDS
OF PIECES AND GAVE WAY TO
GRAVITY.
WORKERS BLOCKED THE SIDEWALK
AND USED A LEAF-BLOWER TO
COLLECT THE SHARDS OF GLASS.
>> I PUT IT ON THE POST WITH
THE PHOTOS I SAID PARTLY
CLOUDY WITH A CHANCE OF
FALLING GLASS.
THAT IS WHAT IT SEEMS LIKE.
YOU JUST CAN'T PREDICT.
>> THIS WAS MY COMMUTE ALONG
HERE.
>> Kevin: DERMOND SAID THEY
ARE USING THE PLANTERS WITH
THE RAILINGS TO KEEP
PEDESTRIANS OUT OF THE LINE OF
FIRE.
THEY HAVE HAD A SCAFFOLDING
OUT FRON FOR A YEAR AND A HALF
NOW.
THEY HAVE HAD TO IMPROVISE AND
COVER IT WITH THE DECORATIVE
BAMBOO POLES.
>> IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT TO
UNDERSTAND WHY IT IS
HAPPENING.
>> Kevin: TODAY CARR
PROPERTIES TOLD US THE
BUILDING MADE OF 100% TEMPERED
SAFETY GLASS THAT BREAKS INTO
GRANULAR PIECES.
THEY ACKNOWLEDGE THE ISSUE BUT
CARR SAYS ONLY 1% OF THE
WINDOW PANES HAVE SHATTERED
AND THE GLASS CONSULTANTS TELL
THEM THAT THE RISK OF
ADDITIONAL BREAKS WILL DECLINE
WITH TIME.
FOR NOW THEY PLAN TO INSTALL
MORE OVERHEAD CANOPIES THIS
SPRING TO REDUCE CHANCE OF
INJURING SOMEONE BELOW.
IN DOWNTOWN BETHESDA, I'M
KEVIN LEWIS, ABC7 NEWS.
>> Jonathan: SIRENS BLARING,
AND FERRETS RUNNING TO A
MARYLAND -- FIREFIGHTERS
RUNNING INTO A MARYLAND HOME
BUT THEY ARRIVED WITH A
SPECIALEDLIRY.
ARRIVE TO MAKE FAMILY DREAMS
COME TRUE.
>> Michelle: GROUP OF
OFFICERS SURROUNDING ONE OF
THEIR OWN SQUAD CARS.
WANTS TO GO IN.
THE DEADLY WILD ANIMAL INSIDE
AND
>> Jonathan: THREE PEOPLE
SHOT ONE BY THE FORT DUPONT
ICE ARENA.
WING WAS IN BAD SHOT AND TWO
OTHERS ARE EXPECTED TO BE
OKAY.
THERE WAS ALSO A SHOOTING ON
STANTON ROAD WHERE THEY HAD TO
USE C.P.R. TO BRING A VICTIM
BACK TO LIFE.
HE IS NOW CONSCIOUS AND ON THE
WAY TO THE HOSPITAL.
NEW ARREST IN THE ARUNDEL
MILLS MALL SHOOTING.
>> THE 16-YEAR-OLD WANTED
TURNED HIMSELF IN.
[bleep]
>> Jonathan: THE SHOOTING
CAUGHT ON CELL PHONE VIDEO AND
POSTED ON INSTAGRAM.
JAMARI HAMMOND FATING
ATTEMPTED MURDER CHARGES.
>> Michelle: TAKE A LOOK AND
ALSO LISTEN.
OH, MY GOSH!
YOU HEAR IT HISSING?
THIS IS A LARGE RATTLESNAKE IN
THE BACK OF THE SQUAD CAR.
A HOMELESS MAN FOUND WALKING
AROUND WITH IT.
OFFICERS ARRIVE AND TOLD HIM
TO TOSS IT IN THE BACK.
>> HOMELESS MAN WALKING AROUND
WITH RATTLESNAKE?
>> Michelle: SO MANY
QUESTIONS.
ALWAYS OUT OF FLORIDA, THE
WILD STORIES.
>> Jonathan: ALWAYS FLORIDA.
COMING UP NEXT AT 7 ZEPHYR --
>>  -- COMING UP NEXT ON 7 --
>> THE BEST FEELING IN THE
WORLD.
>> THE MOMENT THAT THE
COUPLE'S YEAR LONG DREAM CAME
TRUE.
>> Bill: A GREAT STORY
THERE.
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE
OUTSIDE.
THE EVENING FORECAST IS
CALLING FOR THE DRY
CONDITIONS, INCREASING CLOUDS
AND THE TEMPERATURES IN THE
30s.
GREAT TIME TO PREP.
FULL DETAILS COMING UP.
Z3670Z ZI0Z
Y3670Y YI0Y
Z3671Z ZI0Z
Y3671Y YI0Y
>> Jonathan: THE MAN ACCUSED
OF SETTING A FIRE AT COMET
PING-PONG APPEARED IN COURT
TODAY.
YOU CAN SEE FROM THE SKETCHES,
THAT IS A STUFFED MONKEY
SITTING IN COURT TODAY.
NO KIDDING.
HE IS NOW INDICTED ON A
FEDERAL ARSON CHARGE AND HE
WAS ARRESTED AFTER THE POLICE
HAD TO USE A STUN GUN ON HIM
ON A WASHINGTON MONUMENT.
TODAY THE JUDGE RULED HE
SHOULD BE HELD UNTIL THE NEXT
COURT DATE.
A DOZEN STATES INCLUDING
MARYLAND AND VIRGINIA SUING
OVER THE PRESIDENT'S NATIONAL
EMERGENCY DECLARATION.
ONE THAT WOULD FREE UP
BILLIONS OF DOLLARS TO BUILD A
SOUTHERN BORDER WALL.
TONIGHT BOTH SIDES CONFIDENT
THEY WILL COME OUT ON TOP.
>> IT DOES NOT HAVE POWER --
THE PRESIDENT DOES NOT HAVE
POWER TO ACT FRIVOLOUSLY TO
TAKE THE POWER OF THE
DEMOCRACY --
>> WE HAVE A RIGHT TO CALL
NATIONAL SECURITY.
WE NEED THE STRONG BORDERS AND
WE HAVE TO STOP DRUGS AND
CRIME AND CRIMINALS AND THE
HUMAN TRAFFICKING.
WE HAVE TO STOP ALL OF THOSE
THINGS THAT A STRONG WALL WILL
STOP.
>> Jonathan: THE PRESIDENT
PREVIOUSLY SAID HE EXPECTS TO
LOSE IN THE LOWER COURTS BUT
WIN WHEN IT GETS TO THE
SUPREME COURT.
>> Michelle: A BALTIMORE
COUPLE DECIDED TO ADOPT AFTER
DEALING WITH INFERTILITY AND
THE YEAR-LONG WAIT TO BE
PARENTS CAME TO A SWEET END.
THE FIREFIGHTER AND THE NURSE
SURPRISED WITH A BOUNCING BABY
BOY THIS WEEKEND.
VICTORIA SANCHEZ SMOKE TO THE
NEW FAMILY -- SPOKE TO THE NEW
FAMILY IN AN INTERVIEW YOU
WILL SEE ONLY ON 7.
>> Victoria: MICHAEL SAW A
GROUP OF PEOPLE GATHERING IN
FRONT OF HIS HOUSE.
>> I HEAR THEM START TO SING.
SO I HONE IN ON THE FACES AND
I LOOK LIKE, WAIT, I KNOW THE
PEOPLE.
>> Victoria: MICHAEL AND HIS
WIFE KAREN EXPECTED A VISIT
FROM THE ADOPTION AGENCY.
NOT FELLOW FIREFIGHTERS
SINGING A CADENCE FROM THE
ANDMY.
THE COUPLE WAS INITIALLY
SKEPTICAL WITH THE LAST-MINUTE
HOME INVASION.
>> WE WERE SO SHOCKED WHEN WE
OPENED THE DOOR AND SAW FIRE
AND THE AMBULANCE AND THE 30
FIREFIGHTINGS.
>> THEY MIGHT THINK THEY KNOW
THEY ARE GETTING A BABY BUT
NEVER KNOW HOW.
>> THE FOUNDER CALLS THIS THE
GOTCHA DAY.
WHEN THE ADOPTIONS ARE
FINALIZED.
>> BEFORE YOU KNOW IT, WALKING
DOWN THE AISLE OF SOME OF MY
BEST FRIENDS WITH OUR SON.
>> YEAH!
[APPLAUSE]
>> THE BEST FEELING IN THE
WORLD.
SUCH A GIFT THAT THE BIRTH
PARENTS GAVE TO US.
WE HAVE DREAMT ABOUT THIS TIME
FOR SO LONG.
WITHOUT THEM, THIS DREAM WOULD
NEVER COME TRUE.
>> WHO NEEDS A STORK WHEN YOU
HAVE FIREFIGHTERS TO DELIVER A
BEAUTIFUL BOY AND BABY
ESSENTIALS TO YOUR DOORSTEP.
>> WE ARE VERY LUCKY.
VICTORIA SANCHEZ, ABC7 NEWS.
>> Michelle: LOADED.
>> Jonathan: IT DID.
AWESOME.
THEY LOOK RESTED.
THEY ARE HOLDING THE NEW
BUNDLE ON JOY.
>> Michelle: WON'T LAST.
>> Jonathan: COME BACK IN A
COUPLE OF DAYS.
THEY WILL BE GASSED.
>> Bill: CONGRATULATIONS TO
METEOROLOGIST JOSH KNIGHT WHO
JUST TODAY ON HIS SOCIAL MEDIA
PAGE AND WE HAVE ALL REWHEATED
PUT A PICTURE OUT.
>> Michelle: CAROLINE.
>> Bill: THE NEW LITTLE ONE.
>> Michelle: SWEET CAROLINE.
>> Bill: CHECK IT OUT.
SHE IS BEAUTIFUL.
THIS IS A QUIET EVERYTHING.
ABOVE FREEZING BUT WE WILL
DROP.
38 DEGREES HERE IN WARRENTON.
40 AROUND D.C.
34 AT GAITHERSBURG.
SO IT'S OKAY RIGHT NOW.
AND THE CLOUDS ARE OUT.
IT'S DRY.
GREAT TIME TO GO OUT IF YOU
HAVEN'T YET.
YOU CAN PREP, PUT THE SALT
DOWN.
GET THE SNOW BLOWER READY.
GET SHOVELS OUT.
MAYBE.
THE KIDS ARE OFF SCHOOL
TOMORROW SO GET THE WINTER
GEAR READY TO PLAY IN SNOW
THEY WILL WANT TO GET OUT IN
THE MORNING BECAUSE IT'S MESSY
BY THE AFTERNOON AND THE
EVENING.
FOCUS ON THE FUTURE CAST.
HERE WE ARE AT 7:00.
IN THE 30s.
MID-TO-UPPER 30s AROUND THE
REGION.
WE GET TO 11:00
>>> AND FOR THE MOST PART IT'S
BELOW REGION THERE.
MAY BE POCKETS ABOVE.
2:00, STILL DRY.
WATCH FOR 5:00.
THE BLUE IS THE SNOW.
IT WILL MOVE IN.
WHAT IS IMPORTANT IS WHAT THE
ATMOSPHERE DOES HIGHER UP.
EVERYTHING WILL FALL IN SNOW.
THIS IS 7:00 IN THE MORNING.
PLAN FOR A SNOW COMMUTE.
PLAN ON THE SLICK ROADS.
THE SNOW FALL RATE COMING DOWN
IN THE ONE INCH PER HOUR
RANGE.
I SEE IT SNOWING ALL MORNING
LONG THROUGH 12:00 NOON.
WE WILL GET PAST 12:00 NOON.
NOTICE THE PINK.
THAT IS WHERE IT WILL
TRANSITION.
I WANT TO PAUSE THIS AT 2:00.
NOTICE SOME OF THE NUMBERS ARE
STILL AT OR BELOW FREEZING.
BUT YOU SEE THE DIFFERENT
COLOR?
WHAT IS HAPPENING IN THE
ATMOSPHERE IS THE WARMER AIR
FILTERING IN.
SO HIGHER UP THE SNOW IS
MELTING AND BECOMING RAIN.
OR MAYBE EVEN REFREEZING TO A
SLEET PELLET.
THAT IS THE MIX FOR THE
AFTERNOON.
YOU HAVE SNOW AND FREEZING
RAIN ON TOP OF THAT BEFORE
IT'S RAIN.
IT WILL BE MESSY BY THIS TIME
TOMORROW NIGHT.
I SEE US ALL FOR THE MOST PART
TRANSITIONING TO THE RAIN.
THERE WILL BE LINGERING AREAS
WITH THE ICING THAT IS
HAPPENING NORTH AND WEST.
THE COURTS TOMORROW NIGHT WILL
GO WARM ENOUGH, THEY WILL GO
UP OVERNIGHT.
IT WILL BECOME RAIN.
AT 11:00, IN THE MID-30s.
COLD RAIN BUT IT LOOKING LIKE
RAIN TOMORROW NIGHT BEFORE WE
HIT THURSDAY MORNING AND IT
WILL KICK OUT OF HERE.
THURSDAY, BY 12:00 NOON,
40s.
THEN IT IS MID-50s.
SO IT IS MELTING QUICKLY.
FOUR TO SIX INCHES.
THAT IS THE TOTAL AROUND THE
DISTRICT.
TWO TO FOUR AROUND SOUTHERN
MARYLAND.
SOME SPOTS WILL HAVE MORE THAN
SIX INCHES OF SNOW MORE AND
WEST.
BUT IT WON'T SNOW LIKE THAT
AND YOU WAIT AND THURSDAY
MORNING YOU PLAY IN IT.
IT IS GOING TO MELT QUICKLY
WHICH WILL BRING ISSUE OF
LOCALIZED FLOODING.
54 ON THURSDAY.
DRY FRIDAY.
SUNDAY, NOT A TYPO.
70-DEGREE FORECAST.
>> Michelle: WE EARNED THAT.
>> Bill: YES.
>> Michelle: I KNOW ONE
PERSON NOT WORRIED AT ALL
ABOUT THE FORECAST AND ABOUT
ROBERT BURTON.
>> Jonathan: IS ENJOYING THE
70-PLUS DEGREE WEATHER NOW IN
FLORIDA WORKING ON HIS
PITCHING.
RIGHT, ROBERT?
>> Robert: NO.
I BAGGED THAT.
I'M NOT WORKING ON THAT ANY
MORE.
YOU COME TO NATS SPRING
TRAINING AND YOU HAVE THE
SUMEER FANS.
BUT WE HAVE A COUPLE AND THEIR
6-MONTH-OLD SON WHO MIGHT BE
At Redfin, we charge
BUT WEyou a 1% listing fee.EIR
6-MONTH-OLD SON WHO MIGHT BE
SECOND TO NONE IN WEST PALM
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
than the one next door.
Z3458Z ZI0Z
Y3458Y YI0Y
>> Robert: WELCOME BACK TO
BREEZY WEST PALM BEACH,
FLORIDA, FOR THE NATS SPRING
TRAINING.
THIS WAS THE FIRST DAY OF THE
FULL SQUAD WORKOUTS.
THE PITCHERS AND THE CATCHERS
AND THE POSITION PLAYERS
REPORTED YESTERDAY.
THE GANG IS ALL HERE.
MAX SCHERZER AND THE FAN
FAVORITES.
WE SAT DOWN WITH THE PLAYERS
TODAY AND WE ASKED ABOUT THE
EXPECTATIONS.
SAME EVERY YEAR.
WORLD SERIES.
I WILL TELL YOU WHAT ELSE IS
THE SAME.
YOU ALWAYS GET THE SUPER FANS.
WE SPOKE WITH A COUPLE ODE
FROM FLORIDA THAT WILL ALWAYS
BE NATS FANS ALL BECAUSE OF
THEIR 6-MONTH-OLD SON LOGAN.
>> HI!
>> Robert: FOR LITTLE LOGAN
RUPP AND DAVY MARTINEZ, IT'S A
REUNION.
SORT OF.
>> NATIONAL GAME IN MIAMI.
I NEED A BABYSITTER.
COACH?
>> DAVY KNEW LOGAN BEFORE HE
WAS BORN.
HE HELPED LAUREN RUPP MAKE THE
ANNOUNCEMENT TO HER HUSBAND
WILLIAM THE NEXT SPRING
TRAINING.
>> I WENT TO THE COACH SIND I
KNOW THERE IS A LONG SHOT BUT
IF THERE IS ANY CHANCE AT ALL.
I HANDED IT TO HIM.
HE SAID I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN
DO.
>> Robert: "IT" MEANING A
SONOGRAM OF LOGAN.
>> THEY FINISHED WITH
PRACTICE.
>> BRYCE HARPER COMES OVER.
HE IS LIKE CONGRATULATIONS.
WHAT?
FOR YOUR AUTOGRAPH?
HE HANDS ME A SONOGRAM.
I FOUND OUT SHE WAS PREGNANT
WITH THIS DUDE.
>> TO BE BRYCE WITH THE REVEAL
MAKES IT MORE SPECIAL.
>> I'M FROM FLORIDA AND HE
MEANS A LOT TO ME AS THE
NATIONALS FAN.
THE COMEBACK IN THE HOME RUN
DERBY WAS AMAZING.
>> LITTLE LOGAN PITCH TO BRYCE
HARPER MIGHT BEAT OUT $300
MILLION.
>> I HAVE $5.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Robert: SPEAKING OF FREE
AGENCY, A BIG FREE AGENT
SIGNING TODAY WITH THE SAN
DIEGO PADRES.
MANNY MACHADO $300 MILLION
VER TEN YEARS.$300 MILLION
BACK TO YOU IN THE STUDIO.
>> Jonathan: GUARANTEED
MONEY.
>> Bill: A LOT OF MONEY.
>> Jonathan: THANK YOU,
ROBERT.
>> Bill: LATE TONIGHT THE
SNOW MOVES IN 4:00 TO 7:00
A.M.
>> Michelle: THANK YOU,
BILL.
"WORLD NEWS TONIGHT" WITHER
DAVID MUIR UP NEXT.
This is not a bed.
"WORLD NEWS TONIGHT" WITHER
DAVID MUIR UP NEXT.
It's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed is on sale now
from $899, during the
Ultimate Sleep Number Event.
It senses your movement,
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
It even helps with this.
So you wake up ready to
hit the ground running.
Only at a Sleep Number store.
It's the final days
to save 50% on the
Sleep Number 360 Limited
Edition smart bed.
Plus, 24-month financing
on all smart beds.
Ends Sunday.
Sleep Number.
Proven, quality sleep.
♪ We buy any car dot com ♪
♪ we buy any car dot com ♪
♪ ANY ANY ANY ANY ♪
Did you know trading in your car
at a dealer could cost
you money?
A recent study found consumers
who trade in their car
pay an average of $990
dollars more.
So don't trade in...
sell it....
to We Buy Any Car.
Learn more and get your free
online valuation
now at we buy any car dot com
♪ Find out how much your car is
worth at WeBuyAnyCar.com ♪
>>> TONIGHT, THE