>>> TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS AS WE
COME ON THE AIR.
THE FLIGHT TO THE U.S. BOUND FOR
PHILADELPHIA GROUNDED BEFORE IT
COULD TAKE OFF.
ABC NEWS LEARNING JUST MOMENTS
AGO ONE OF THE AMERICAN AIRLINES
PILOTS WAS ARRESTED.
WHAT WE'RE LEARNING RIGHT NOW.
>>> ALSO BREAKING, FIVE REPORTED
TORNADOES AT THIS HOUR.
THE DEADLY STORM MOVING ACROSS
THE COUNTRY.
20 STATES FROM THE DAKOTAS ALL
THE WAY TO THE NORTHEAST
EXPECTING SNOW, ICE AND
FLOODING.
WHITEOUT CONDITIONS, CARS SWEPT
AWAY.
TONIGHT, THE RESCUES, YOU'LL SEE
THEM.
AND ROB HAS THE NEW TRACK.
>>> THE POLITICAL CRISIS IN
VIRGINIA.
UNBELIEVABLY GROWING YET AGAIN
TONIGHT.
FIRST, THE GOVERNOR, THEN THE
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR, THEN THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL.
AND TONIGHT, ANOTHER TOP STATE
LAWMAKER NOW FACING SERIOUS
QUESTIONS.
>>> THE MURDER MYSTERY OUTSIDE
NEW YORK CITY.
THE WOMAN'S BODICE COVERED IN A
SUITCASE.
TONIGHT, WHAT WE'VE NOW LEARNED.
>>> THE URGENT MANHUNT THIS
EVENING FOR THE GUNMAN AFTER A
WIFE WAS KILLED WHILE SETTING UP
FOR A GARAGE SALE.
>>> THE HORRIFIC CASE OF
APPARENT ROAD RAGE.
THE DRIVER OPENING FIRE ON A
SCHOOL BUS, HITTING THE DRIVER
TWICE.
A YOUNG STUDENT ONBOARD.
>>> THE ABC NEWS EXCLUSIVE
TONIGHT IN THE JAYME CLOSS CASE.
SHE WAS ABDUCTED FOR 88 DAYS.
TONIGHT, YOU WILL HEAR FROM THE
ALLEGED KIDNAPPER'S FATHER.
AND HIS VISITS TO THAT HOUSE
WHILE JAYME CLOSS WAS BEING HELD
CAPTIVE UNDER A BED WHAT HIS
ALLEGEDLY DID TO KEEP HER FROM
YELLING FOR HELP.
>>> AND A DEVELOPING STORY ON
JEFF BESOES, ACCUSING "THE
NATIONAL INYEARER".
WHAT HE'S NOW SAYING.
>>> AND TONIGHT, RIGHT HERE, WE
CELEBRATE A BASEBALL LEGEND, A
TRAIL BLAZER AND HIS REMARKABLE
CAREER.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH
US HERE TONIGHT.
WE HAVE SEVERAL DEVELOPING
STORIES, AND WE BEGIN TONIGHT
WITH AMAZON CEO JEFF BEZOS, IN A
BATTLE WITH NATIONAL ENQUIRER.
TONIGHT, HE HAS JUST GONE PUBLIC
WHAT WITH HE SAYS WAS AN
EXTORTION PLOT INVOLVING
COMPROMISING PHOTOS.
WLET'S GET RIGHT TO REBECCA
JARVIS, WHO HAS BEEN FOLLOWING
THIS STORY, EVERY DEVELOPMENT,
WITH WHAT WE'RE LEARNING
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: THIS IS A STUNNING
TURN IN THAT ONGOING BATTLE
BETWEEN JEFF BEZOS AND THE
NATIONAL ENQUIRER.
JUST WEEKS AGO, THIS WAS THE
STORY, THAT THE NATIONAL
ENQUIRER FIRST BROKE ABOUT HIS
AFFAIR.
HE'S NOW QUESTIONED, WAS THAT
POLITICALLY MOTIVATED?
HE'S COME FORWARD TONIGHT
SUGGESTING THAT THE NATIONAL
ENQUIRER WAS TRYING TO BLACKMAIL
AND EXTORT HIM WITH NUDE PHOTOS.
IN A POST TONIGHT, HE SAYS, OF
COURSE, I DON'T WANT THOSE
PHOTOS PUBLISHED, BUT I DON'T
WANT TO PARTICIPATE IN HIS
WELL-KNOWN PRACTICE OF
BLACKMAIL.
WE REACHED OUT TO THE NATIONAL
ENQUIRER, THEY'VE YET TO
RESPOND, DAVID.
>> ALL RIGHT, REBECCA JARVIS
LEADING US OFF TONIGHT.
REBECCA, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS ANOTHER DEVELOPING
HEADLINE AS WE COME ON TONIGHT.
THE ARREST OF AN AMERICAN
AIRLINES PILOT.
THE FLIGHT WAS BOUND FOR THE
U.S., FOR PHILADELPHIA, IN FACT.
THE PASSENGER JET DID NOT TAKE
OFF FROM THE UK.
ONE OF THE PILOTS WAS TAKEN INTO
CUSTODY ON SUSPICION OF BEING
OVER THE LIMIT FOR ALCOHOL
BEFORE FLYING.
ABC'S SENIOR TRANSPORTATION
CORRESPONDENT DAVID KERLEY WITH
THAT STORY.
>> Reporter: BRITISH AUTHORITIES
DETAINED THE AMERICAN AIRLINES
FLIGHT CREW MEMBER IN MANCHESTER
BEFORE THE A-330 TOOK OFF FOR
PHILADELPHIA.
AN AVIATION SOURCE TELLING ABC
NEWS, IT WAS ONE OF THE THREE
PILOTS, BUT IT IS UNCLEAR IF IT
WAS THE CAPTAIN OR ONE OF THE
FIRST OFFICERS WHO TONIGHT IS
BEING INVESTIGATED FOR
"SUSPICION OF PERFORMING AN
AVIATION FUNCTION WHEN OVER THE
PRESCRIBED LIMIT OF ALCOHOL."
AMERICAN CANCELED THAT FLIGHT,
REBOOKING PASSENGERS AND SAYING
IN A STATEMENT, "SAFETY IS OUR
HIGHEST PRIORITY AND WE
APOLOGIZE TO OUR CUSTOMERS."
THE LIMIT FOR ALCOHOL IN PILOTS
IS HALF THAT FOR DRIVERS, .04.
THIS PILOT ARRESTED TWO YEARS
AGO IN DETROIT.
AND SOME LIKE THIS FORMER
JETBLUE PILOT FACED FEDERAL
CHARGES.
DID YOU PUT 270 PASSENGERS AT
RISK?
>> NO COMMENT.
>> THIS IS AN ONGOING ISSUE
YOU'VE REPORTED ON BEFORE.
DAVID KERLEY WITH US TONIGHT.
WE'RE AWARE OF THIS LATEST
ARREST, AND HAS AMERICAN
AIRLINES TAKEN ANY ACTION, OTHER
THAN CANCELING THE FLIGHT,
DAVID?
>> Reporter: NO, SO FAR, THAT'S
ALL THEY'VE DONE.
AMERICAN SAYS THEY ARE
COOPERATING WITH THE BRITISH
AUTHORITIES WHO ARE
INVESTIGATING THIS INCIDENT.
DAVID?KERLEY, THANK YOU.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT, THE DEADLY
STORM ON THE MOVE AT THIS HOUR.
50 MILLION AMERICANS UNDER
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORIES.
BLIZZARD CONDITIONS, SNOW, ICE
AND AT LEAST FIVE REPORTED
TORNADOES AT THIS HOUR.
BLIZZARD WARNINGS AND BLINDING
SNOW IN MINNESOTA.
LIGHTNING, PART OF AN ICE STORM
IN MISSOURI, COATING TREES,
DOWNING BRANCHES AND POWER LINES
THERE.
CARS IN THIS BUS UNDER WATER IN
TENNESSEE.
AND FIERCE WINDS DERAILING TRAIN
CARS IN MISSOURI.
20 STATES FROM THE DAKOTAS DOWN
TO TENNESSEE, ALL THE WAY UP TO
THE NORTHEAST.
WHERE IT HITS TONIGHT.
ABC'S ALEX PEREZ IN THE STORM
ZONE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, DARING
HIGH WATER RESCUES ACROSS MIDDLE
TENNESSEE.
THAT POWERFUL WINTER STORM
DUMPING A MONTH'S WORTH OF RAIN
IN JUST HOURS.
FIRST RESPONDERS USING
FLASHLIGHTS TO REACH THIS
SUBMERGED CAR, PICKING TWO
PEOPLE TO SAFETY.
>> WE'RE GOING TO NEED SOME
HANDS GETTING THEM UP THE HILL.
>> Reporter: AT LEAST ONE PERSON
SWEPT AWAY AND KILLED ELSEWHERE
IN THE STATE.
ALL THAT RAIN WASHING AWAY
ROADS.
THIS IS WHAT'S LEFT OF STATE
ROUTE 66.
IN SOUTHEAST MISSOURI, HOWLING
WIND GUSTS KNOCKING THIS TRAIN
OFF ITS TRACKS.
TORNADOES REPORTED IN SEVERAL
STATES.
MEANWHILE, IN THE NORTHERN
PLAINS, BLIZZARD CONDITIONS UP
TO A FOOT OF SNOW CLOSING
INTERSTATES.
VISIBILITY SO POOR IN ST. CLOUD,
MINNESOTA, THIS STORMCHASER
NEARLY SLAMMING INTO A TRACTOR
TRAILER.
>> WHOA!
>> Reporter: IN THE MIDWEST, UP
TO HALF AN INCH OF ICE COATING
ROADS, TREES AND POWER LINES,
THREATENING TO KNOCK OUT POWER
TO THOUSANDS.
IN OVERLAND PARK, KANSAS, A HIGH
SCHOOL PRINCIPAL TAKING A TUMBLE
OUT OF HIS TRUCK.
HE POSTED THE VIDEO WITH A
LAUGH, BUT THE ICE, NO JOKE.
IN ILLINOIS, A BRIEF THAW
CAUSING MAJOR ICE JAMS ALONG A
FROZEN KANKAKEE RIVER.
HOMEOWNERS LIKE JOJO BROADWELL,
WHO LIVE ALONG THE RIVER,
BRACING FOR THE WORST.
>> IT'S LIKE A BULLDOZER COMING
UP.
THERE'S NOTHING STOPPING THIS
ICE.
IT WILL DESTROY ANYTHING IN ITS
PATH.
>> AND DAVID, I WANT TO SHOW YOU
WHY THERE IS SO MUCH CONCERN
HERE.
THERE IS A HOME RIGHT HERE.
AND IF WALK WITH ME, 20 FEET
AWAY, THERE'S A GROWING ICEBERG
SLOWLY CREEPING INTO THE
BACKYARD HERE.
LUCKILY, OFFICIALS SAY, THE
RIVER IS NOW MOVING AND THE
WATER IS RECEDING.
DAVID?
>> ALEX, THANK YOU.
LET'S GET RIGHT TO ROB MARCIANO,
LIVE WITH US TONIGHT, TRACKING
IT ALL AS THIS MOVES EAST.
HI, ROB.
>> Reporter: HI, DAVID.
THIS STORM HAS REALLY STRETCHED
OUT.
WE HAD FOUR STATES REPORTING
TORNADOES, NOT TO MENTION THE
FLOODING AND THE SNOW.
BLIZZARD WARNINGS UP FOR
MINNESOTA AND THE FLASH FLOOD
WATCHES FOR NEARLY ALL OF OHIO.
HERE COMES THE HEAVY RAIN.
GOING TO BE IN THE NORTHEAST FOR
THE MORNING RUSH, WITH A LITTLE
BIT OF MIXING OF WINTER
PRECIPITATION.
AND MUCH COLDER.
WE SNAP BACK TO WINTER.
30 BELOW IN MINNEAPOLIS TOMORROW
FOR A MORNING WIND CHILL AND
ANOTHER WINTER STORM COMING FOR
SEATTLE.
SIGNIFICANT SNOW EVENT BEGINNING
THERE TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
DAVID?
>> ROB MARCIANO TRACKING IT FOR
US.
THANK YOU, ROB.
>>> WE'RE GOING TO TURN NEXT TO
THE POLITICAL CRISIS IN
VIRGINIA, AND IN AN UNBELIEVABLE
TURN, GROWING YET AGAIN TONIGHT.
FIRST, IT WAS THE GOVERNOR UNDER
PRESSURE TO RESIGN FOR THAT
RACIST IMAGE IN HIS MEDICAL
SCHOOL YEARBOOK, THEN THE
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR, WHO WOULD
SERVE NEXT, HE'S FACING THAT
ALLEGATION OF SEXUAL ASSAULT,
FOLLOWED BY THE STATE ATTORNEY
GENERAL, REVEALING HE WORE
BLACKFACE ONCE IN COLLEGE.
ALL THREE DEMOCRATS.
AND NOW, TONIGHT, ANOTHER TOP
LAWMAKER, A REPUBLICAN, FACING
QUESTIONS ABOUT HIS PAST.
ABC'S CHIEF NATIONAL AFFAIRS
CORRESPONDENT TOM LLAMAS FROM
RICHMOND, THE STATE CAPITAL.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT IN
VIRGINIA, GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM
HAS ALL BUT VANISHED.
NO WORD FROM HIM AT ALL IN A
NEARLY A WEEK.
AN AVALANCHE OF HEADLINES
TELLING THE TALE, "STATE OF
TURMOIL," "POLITICAL CRISIS
ESCALATES," "WHAT NEXT?"
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR, HOW ARE YOU
DOING?
TOM LLAMAS FROM ABC NEWS.
VIRGINIA'S SECOND
HIGHEST RANKING ELECTED
OFFICIAL, LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR
JUSTIN FAIRFAX, NOW FENDING OFF
AN ALLEGATION OF SEXUAL ASSAULT.
DR. VANESSA TYSON ALLEGING HE
FORCED HER TO PERFORM ORAL SEX
IN A HOTEL ROOM AT THE
2004 DEMOCRATIC NATIONAL
CONVENTION.
FAIRFAX SAYS THEIR ENCOUNTER WAS
CONSENSUAL.
DO YOU REMEMBER DR. TYSON EVER
CRYING?
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU, MAN.
>> Reporter: DO YOU REMEMBER
DR. TYSON EVER CRYING?
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU GUYS.
WE'RE HEADING TO SESSION.
>> Reporter: NOW, SOME NATIONAL
DEMOCRATS, EVEN THOUGH RUNNING
FOR PRESIDENT, CALLING FOR AN
INVESTIGATION.
>> THE LETTER WRITTEN BY THE
WOMAN READS AS A CREDIBLE
ACCOUNT.
>> Reporter: THE STATE'S
THIRD-HIGHEST RANKING OFFICIAL,
ATTORNEY GENERAL MARK HERRING,
ANOTHER DEMOCRAT, ALSO ENGULFED
IN SCANDAL AFTER ADMITTING HE,
TOO, WORE BLACKFACE ONCE IN THE
1980s.
AND NOW, A FOURTH TOP OFFICIAL
COMING UNDER FIRE, AS WELL.
THIS TIME, A REPUBLICAN.
THE VIRGINIA PILOT NEWSPAPER
REPORTING THAT SENATE MAJORITY
LEADER THOMAS NORMAN WAS
MANAGING EDITOR OF THE 1968
YEARBOOK OF THE VIRGINIA
MILITARY INSTITUTE, WHICH
FEATURED SEVERAL STUDENTS IN
BLACKFACE AND CONTAINED RACIAL
SLURS.
SENATOR, DO YOU REGRET WHAT'S IN
THE YEARBOOK?
DO YOU REGRET IT?
DO YOU APOLOGIZE AT ALL?
>> I'M HERE TO TALK ABOUT THE
BUDGET.
>> Reporter: THE SENATOR LATER
SAYING HE WAS NOT IN ANY OF
THOSE PHOTOS AND HE ADVOCATED
FOR RACIAL INTEGRATION WHILE AT
VMI.
IS THERE ANYTHING WE CAN ALL
LEARN FROM WHAT'S HAPPENED HERE
IN VIRGINIA THE LAST FEW DAYS?
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
ANYTHING THAT WE ALL CAN LEARN,
BUT I WILL SAY THAT PROBABLY IN
THE NEWS MEDIA, YOU'RE SMARTER
WHEN YOU LOOK IN THE REARVIEW
MIRROR.
>> TOM LLAMAS WITH US TONIGHT
FROM THE STATE CAPITAL IN
RICHMOND, VIRGINIA.
AND TOM, WORD TONIGHT THAT THE
GOVERNOR, GOVERNOR NORTHAM, HAS
REACHED OUT TO THE LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
AFTER DAYS OF NO COMMUNICATION,
THE GOVERNOR AND THE LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR SPOKE THIS MORNING.
WE UNDERSTAND THAT CONVERSATION
WITH CORDIAL.
BOTH MEN WISHED EACH OTHER WELL.
AND AT ONE POINT, THEY BOTH SAID
THEY WERE PRAYING FOR EACH
OTHER.
DAVID?
>> TOM LLAMAS AGAIN TONIGHT.
THANK YOU, TOM.
>>> THIS EVENING, THE MANHUNT
FOR A KILLER IN TEXAS IS UNDER
WAY, AFTER A WOMAN WAS KILLED
WHILE SETTING UP A GARAGE SALE.
SURVEILLANCE SHOWING THE GUNMAN
APPROACHING THE WOMAN IN HER
DRIVEWAY, EXCHANGING SOME WORDS
AND THEN FIRING POINT BLANK.
TONIGHT, POLICE ARE NOW ASKING
FOR THE PUBLIC'S HELP, AND ABC'S
MARCUS MOORE IS ON THE SCENE.
>> Reporter: THIS TERRIFYING
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO SHOWING
ELIZABETH BARRAZA'S
EXECUTION-STYLE MURDER HAS
INVESTIGATORS OUTSIDE OF HOUSTON
PUZZLED.
JUST FOUR MINUTES AFTER HER
HUSBAND LEFT FOR WORK, THE
29-YEAR-OLD WAS MURDERED WHILE
SETTING UP A GARAGE SALE IN HER
OWN DRIVEWAY.
THAT SUSPECT, SHOOTING BARRAZA
FOUR TIMES AT POINT BLANK RANGE
EARLY IN THE MORNING ON
JON 25th, THEN RUNNING AWAY ON
FOOT BEFORE DRIVING OFF IN THIS
DARK-COLORED TRUCK.
POLICE SAY IT'S UNCLEAR WHETHER
BARRAZA WAS TARGETED.
SHE HAD ONLY PUT OUT SIGNS FOR
THAT GARAGE SALE THAT MORNING.
AND INVESTIGATORS DON'T EVEN
KNOW IF THE SHOOTER IS A MAN OR
A WOMAN.
>> DEFINITELY IT IS POSSIBLE
THEY WERE TRYING TO DISGUISE
THEIR APPEARANCE.
>> Reporter: HER FAMILY MAKING A
PLEA FOR THE PUBLIC TO HELP FIND
THE KILLER.
>> WE HAD TO TRADE OUR FIFTH
ANNIVERSARY FOR HER FUNERAL.
>> Reporter: AND DAVID, THIS
GARAGE SALE IN THE DRIVEWAY HERE
WAS TO RAISE MONEY FOR AN
ANNIVERSARY TRIP WITH HER
HUSBAND.
AUTHORITIES SAY THEY HAVE
GENERATED NEW LEADS OVERNIGHT,
BUT THIS CASE REMAINS A MYSTERY.
DAVID?
>> ALL RIGHT, MARCUS, THANK YOU.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP TONIGHT IS
LASHING OUT, AS DEMOCRATS WHO
NOW CONTROL THE HOUSE HAVE
STEPPED UP THEIR OVERSIGHT.
THE PRESIDENT CALLING IT, QUOTE,
PRESIDENTIAL HARASSMENT, SAYING
THE DEMS ARE, QUOTE, GOING NUTS.
HOUSE SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI
PUSHING BACK TONIGHT, CALLING
THE SCRUTINY ON THE PRESIDENT
THEIR CONSTITUTIONAL SPOT, AND
TONIGHT, ONE TARGET?
THE PRESIDENT'S TAXES.
ABC'S MARY BRUCE UP ON THE HILL.
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS IN
CONGRESS ARE KICKING THEIR
INVESTIGATIONS OF THE TRUMP
PRESIDENCY INTO HIGH GEAR.
>> I THINK OVERWHELMINGLY THE
PUBLIC WANTS TO SEE THE
PRESIDENT'S TAX RETURNS.
>> Reporter: UNLIKE PREVIOUS
PRESIDENTS, TRUMP HAS REFUSED TO
RELEASE HIS RETURNS.
>> I'M NOT RELEASING THE TAX
RETURNS, BECAUSES YOU KNOW,
THEY'RE UNDER AUDIT.
>> Reporter: BUT NOW, DEMOCRATS
HAVE THE POWER TO GO AFTER THEM.
>> WE WILL ASK THE QUESTION,
DOES THE PUBLIC HAVE A NEED TO
KNOW THAT A PERSON SEEKING TO
HOLD THE HIGHEST OFFICE IN OUR
COUNTRY OBEYS THE TAX LAW?
>> Reporter: WITH DEMOCRATS
DIGGING IN, THE PRESIDENT IS
LASHING OUT, TWEETING,
"UNLIMITED PRESIDENTIAL
HARASSMENT.
THE DEMS AND THEIR COMMITTEES
ARE GOING NUTS."
IS THERE ANY CONCERN THAT YOU'RE
IN DANGER OF APPEARING LIKE
YOU'RE OVERREACHING?
>> WHATEVER THE PRESIDENT SAYS
ABOUT US, HE'S PROJECTING HIS
OWN UNRULINESS.
HE'S A PROJECTOR, AND THAT'S
WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
>> Reporter: THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE IS
LAUNCHING A SWEEPING
INVESTIGATION INTO THE
PRESIDENT, HIS FAMILY, HIS
FINANCES AND POSSIBLE RUSSIA
TIES.
AND TONIGHT, A STANDOFF BETWEEN
THE HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE
AND THE PRESIDENT'S ACTING
ATTORNEY GENERAL, MATTHEW
WHITAKER.
COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN GERALD NADLER
THREATENED TO SUBPOENA WHITAKER
IF HE DOESN'T SHOW UP AT A
SCHEDULED HEARING TOMORROW.
WHITAKER THEN REFUSING TO APPEAR
UNLESS THE CONGRESSMAN DROPS
THAT THREAT.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO, LET'S GET TO
MARY BRUCE LIVE, BECAUSE THERE
ARE FAST-MOVING PARTS ON THIS
STORY TONIGHT.
JUST MOMENTS AGO, MARY, THE
WHITE HOUSE RELEASING A
STATEMENT ABOUT THE ACTING
ATTORNEY GENERAL?
>> Reporter: YES, AND DAVID, THE
CHAIRMAN HERE STILL ISN'T RULING
OUT THAT SUBPOENA, SAYING IT
DEPENDS ON HOW WHITAKER ANSWERS
THEIR QUESTIONS, IF HE SHOWS UP
HERE TOMORROW.
BUT TONIGHT, THE WHITE HOUSE
SAYS THE CHAIRMAN IS, QUOTE,
PLAYING POINTLESS POLITICAL
GAMES.
DAVID?
>> MARY BRUCE, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW, TO AN ABC NEWS
EXCLUSIVE TONIGHT, IN THE CASE
OF JAYME CLOSS.
THE FATHER OF HER ACCUSED
KIDNAPPER IS NOW BREAKING HIS
SILENCE.
HIS SON, JAKE PATTERSON, IS
ACCUSED OF HOLDING KLOSS CAPTIVE
FOR 88 DAYS AFTER KILLING HER
PARENTS.
TONIGHT, HIS FATHER, WHO
ACTUALLY VISITED THAT HOME, NOT
KNOWING CLOSS WAS THERE.
HERE'S ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS.
>> Reporter: JAKE PATTERSON IS
ACCUSED OF ABDUCTING JAYME CLOSS
AND KILLING HER PARENTS, AND NOW
HIS FATHER IS SPEAKING
EXCLUSIVELY TO ABC NEWS.
>> I MOST DEFINITELY WANT
JAYME'S FAMILY, EVERYONE, TO
KNOW THAT OUR HEARTS ARE BROKEN
FOR THEIR FAMILY.
>> Reporter: ON WEDNESDAY,
PATTERSON MADE HIS FIRST COURT
APPEARANCE.
>> AND DO YOU UNDERSTAND THE
CHARGES AGAINST YOU AT THIS
TIME?
>> YES.
>> Reporter: PATRICK PATTERSON
IS STILL STRUGGLING TO MAKE
SENSE OF IT ALL.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO HUMBLY ASK
PEOPLE TO PRAY FOR A COMPLETE
HEALING OF JAYME'S HEART, MIND
AND SOUL.
>> Reporter: PATTERSON ALLEGEDLY
TARGETED THE 13-YEAR-OLD AFTER
SEEING HER BOARD A SCHOOL BUS IN
OCTOBER, TELLING POLICE, "HE
KNEW THAT WAS THE GIRL HE WAS
GOING TO TAKE."
HE'S ACCUSED OF KILLING JAYME'S
PARENTS IN A HOME INVASION AND
HOLDING HER CAPTIVE FOR 88 DAYS
AT HIS HOME WHERE, SHE SAYS, HE
BARRICADED HER UNDER HIS BED FOR
12 HOURS AT A TIME UNTIL SHE
ESCAPED.
>> I'M VERY SORRY FOR EVERYTHING
THAT HAS HAPPENED.
>> Reporter: PATTERSON ALLEGEDLY
CONFESSED THAT THERE WERE
MULTIPLE TIMES WHEN HIS FATHER
WOULD COME OVER AND WAS JUST
FEET AWAY FROM JAYME AND HAD NO
IDEA, BECAUSE SHE WAS BARRICADED
UNDER THE BED WITH THE RADIO
TURNED UP.
DAVID?
>> WOW.
ALL RIGHT, LINSEY DAVIS WITH THE
EXCLUSIVE TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS THURSDAY.
CELEBRATING A BASEBALL LEGEND
TONIGHT.
A TRUE TRAIL BLAZER.
>>> ALSO, THE HORRIFIC CASE OF
APPARENT ROAD RAGE.
NEW IMAGES TONIGHT, THE DRIVER
OPENING FIRE ON A SCHOOL BUS,
HITTING THE DRIVER TWICE.
THERE WAS A YOUNG STUDENT
ONBOARD.
>>> THE MURDER HISTORY OUTSIDE
NEW YORK CITY TONIGHT.
THE WOMAN'S BODICE COVERED IN A
SUITCASE, AND THIS EVENING, WHAT
WE'VE NOW LEARNED ABOUT HER
IDENTITY.
>>> AND THE STUNNING IMAGE THIS
EVENING.
THE YOUNG GIRL SAVED AFTER 18
HOURS BURIED UNDER THE RUBBLE OF
A COLLAPSED BUILDING.
YOU WILL SEE THE MOMENT SHE IS
RUSHED TO SAFETY.
A LOT MORE NEWS AHEAD TONIGHT.
d:
When it comes to managing
your type 2 diabetes,
what matters to you?
Let's see.
Most of you say lower A1C.
But only a few of you
are thinking about your heart.
Fact is, even though
it helps to manage A1C,
type 2 diabetes still
increases your risk
of a fatal heart
attack or stroke.
JARDIANCE is the first
type 2 diabetes pill
with a lifesaving
cardiovascular benefit
for adults who have type 2
diabetes and heart disease,
JARDIANCE significantly
reduces the risk of dying
from a cardiovascular event
and lowers A1C,
with diet and exercise.
Let's give it another try.
JARDIANCE can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration.
This may cause you
to feel dizzy, faint,
or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis
is a serious side effect
that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting, stomach pain,
tiredness,
and trouble breathing.
A rare but life-threatening
bacterial infection
in the skin of the genital
area could also occur.
Stop taking JARDIANCE
and call your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of this bacterial infection,
ketoacidosis
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic
reaction include rash,
swelling, and difficulty
breathing or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects are
sudden kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about
all the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
Isn't it time to rethink your
type 2 diabetes medication?
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE
and get to the heart
of what matters.
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE
98% of us don't get enough
omega-3s.
Which is why MegaRed Advanced
4in1
packs more omega-3 power into
one small softgel.
It supports your heart...
Brain... Eyes... And joints.
MegaRed.
>>> WE'RE GOING TO TURN NOW TO
THAT APPARENT ROAD RAGE SHOOTING
IN MINNEAPOLIS.
A DRIVER SHOOTING A SCHOOL BUS
DRIVER AND HITTING THE BUS
DRIVER TWICE.
HERE'S ABC'S CLAYTON SANDELL
WITH THE NEW SURVEILLANCE.
>> Reporter: WHAT POLICE SAY
STARTED AS A FENDER BENDER
BETWEEN A CAR AND A SCHOOL BUS,
TONIGHT, A CASE OF ATTEMPTED
MURDER.
CAPTURED TUESDAY ON THIS
MINNEAPOLIS TRAFFIC CAMERA,
POLICE SAY THIS IS 31-YEAR-OLD
KENNETH LILLY, STOPPED IN
TRAFFIC, WALKING TOWARDS THE BUS
AFTER IT APPARENTLY BUMPED HIS
CAR.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE THE GUY IS IN
SOME SORT OF SECURITY UNIFORM OR
SOMETHING.
LOOKS LIKE HE IS -- DOES HAVE A
WEAPON ON HIM.
>> Reporter: WHEN THE BUS DRIVER
REFUSES TO LET LILLY ONBOARD
BECAUSE THERE'S AN 8-YEAR-OLD
GIRL IN THE BACK, POLICE SAY
LILLY PULLS A .9 MILLIMETER
HANDGUN, AND YOU CAN SEE THE
FLASHES, OPENS FIRE, STRIKING
THE BUS DRIVER IN THE ARM AND
GRAZING HIS HEAD.
>> PULLED OVER ON THE LEFT
SHOULDER, I'VE GOT HIM ON
CAMERA.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY LILLY
THEN CALLS 911.
OFFICERS ARRIVING MOMENTS LATER
AND TAKE HIM INTO CUSTODY.
INVESTIGATORS SAY LILLY TOLD
THEM HE FEARED FOR HIS LIFE.
BUT PROSECUTORS SAY THE VIDEO
SHOWS HE WAS IN NO DANGER.
>> WE DO NOT BELIEVE THERE WAS A
SELF DEFENSE CLAIM BASED UPON
THE EVIDENCE WE HAVE RECEIVED SO
FAR.
>> Reporter: LILLY IS CHARGED
WITH ATTEMPTED MURDER AND
ASSAULT.
THE BUS DRIVER, EXPECTED TO BE
OKAY AND HIS 8-YEAR-OLD
PASSENGER WAS NOT HURT.
DAVID?
>> THANK YOU, CLAYTON.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, A WOMAN
DISCOVERED IN A SUITCASE IN NEW
YORK.
>>> AND TOMORROW, WHAT'S COMING
UP ON "20/20."
A STORY WE'VE COVERED FOR YEARS.
>>> A MOTHER, A WIFE, HER FIRST
HUSBAND, DEKD.
HER SECOND HUSBAND, DEAD.
THEN, HER DAUGHTER POISONS.
NOW, NEW DETAILS, AND THE DAVID
MUIR PRISON INTERVIEW THAT MADE
HEADLINES.
>> STACY CASTER IS CONVICTED OF
MURDERING HER HUSBAND, CONVICTED
OF ATTEMPTED MURDER OF HER OWN
DAUGHTER.
AND SHE'S WALKING TOWARDS US AND
WE WONDER, WHAT IS SHE GOING TO
SAY THIS TIME?
>> THE "20/20" EVENT, FRIDAY ON
ABC.
family and FARXIGA,
the pill that starts with "f."
FARXIGA, along with
diet and exercise,
helps lower A1C in adults
with type 2 diabetes.
It's one pill a day.
And although it's not a
weight-loss drug,
it may help you lose weight.
Do not take if
allergic to FARXIGA.
If you experience symptoms
of a serious allergic reaction
such as rash, swelling,
difficulty breathing
or swallowing,
stop taking and seek
medical help right away.
Do not take FARXIGA if you
have severe kidney problems,
are on dialysis or
have bladder cancer.
Tell your doctor right
away if you have blood
or red color in your urine
or pain while you urinate.
FARXIGA can cause serious side
effects including dehydration,
genital yeast infections
in women and men,
serious urinary
tract infections,
low blood sugar,
and kidney problems.
Stop taking FARXIGA and
call your doctor right away
if you have signs
of ketoacidosis
which is serious and
may lead to death.
Ask your doctor about the pill
that starts with "f"
and visit FARXIGA.com
for savings.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may be
able to help.
If you can't afford
your medication,
Hey, Darryl!
Hey, Thomas.
If you were choosing a network,
would you want the one
the experts at
RootMetrics say
is number one
in the nation?
Sure, they probably know
what they're talking about.
Or the one
that J.D. Power says
is highest in
network quality
by people
who use it every day?
This is a tough one.
Well, not really,
because Verizon won both.
So you don't even
have to choose.
Why didn't you just
lead with that?
It's like a fun thing.
(VO)
Chosen by experts.
Chosen by you.
Get 50 million songs now
with Apple Music included,
on us.
On both iOS and Android.
It's the unlimited plan you need
on the network you deserve.
I work hard to protect
this Tookus.
To take care of any
messy situations.
And put irritation in its place.
And if I can get comfortable
keeping this Tookus
safe and protected...
you can get comfortable doing
the same with yours.
PREPARATION H.
Get comfortable with it.
Oh, wow. You two are going to
have such a great trip.
Thanks to you, we will.
This is why Voya helps reach
today's goals...
all while helping you to and
through retirement.
Can you help with these?
We're more of the plan, invest
and protect kind of help...
Voya. Helping you to and through
retirement.
Woman:
This is your wake-up call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis,
month after month,
the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
HUMIRA can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
HUMIRA targets and blocks
a source of inflammation
that contributes
to joint pain
and irreversible damage.
VO: HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections
including tuberculosis,
and cancers, including
lymphoma, have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Woman:
Help stop the clock
on further irreversible
joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here. Right now.
HUMIRA.
>>> TO THE INDEX, AND TO THE
MURDER MYSTERY IN CONNECTICUT.
POLICE NOW IDENTIFYING THE
VICTIM.
VALERIE RACE WAS FOUND STUFFED
IN A SUITCASE ON THE SIDE OF THE
ROAD.
SHE WAS REPORTED MISSING FROM
NEW YORK A WEEK AGO WHEN SHE
FAILED TO SHOW UP AT WORK.
HER MOTHER SAYS HER DAUGHTER
FEARED FOR HER OWN SAFETY BEFORE
SHE VANISHED, AND POLICE ARE
STILL SEARCHING FOR THE KILLER
TONIGHT.
>>> AND THE IMAGE OVERSEAS THIS
EVENING, THE AMAZING RESCUE IN
TURKEY.
A 5-YEAR-OLD GIRL PULLED ALIVE
FROM THE RUBBLE.
18 HOURS AFTER AN EIGHT-STORY
BUILDING COLLAPSED IN ISTANBUL.
AT LEAST TEN PEOPLE WERE KILLED.
RESCUERS BELIEVE THERE MAY BE
MORE SURVIVORS STILL.
THE CAUSE IS STILL UNDER
INVESTIGATION.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK TONIGHT,
CELEBRATING A BASEBALL LEGEND.
A TRAIL BLAZER.
AND WHAT WE UNEARTHED TODAY, IN
A MOMENT.
If you have postmenopausal
osteoporosis
and a high risk for fracture
now might not be the best time
to ask yourself
are my bones strong?
Life is full of make-or-break
moments.
That's why it's so important
to help reduce your risk of
fracture with Prolia®.
Only Prolia® is proven to help
strengthen
and protect bones from fracture
with 1 shot every 6 months.
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take
XGEVA®.
Serious allergic reactions,
like low blood pressure; trouble
breathing;
throat tightness; face, lip, or
tongue swelling;
rash; itching; or hives have
happened.
Tell your doctor about dental
problems
as severe jaw bone problems may
happen
or new or unusual pain in your
hip groin, or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone fractures
have occurred.
Speak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects,
like low blood calcium, serious
infections,
which could need
hospitalization, skin problems,
and severe bone, joint, or
muscle pain.
Are you ready?
Ask your doctor how Prolia® can
help strengthen your bones.
Gentle means everything,
so we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients
Added one handed pumps
And beat the
top safety standards
The new JOHNSON'S®
Choose Gentle
Building a better bank
starts with looking
at something old,
and saying, "really?"
So Capital One is building
something completely new.
Capital One Cafes.
Inviting places with
people here to help you,
not sell you.
And savings and
checking accounts with
no fees or minimums.
Because that's
how it should be.
You can open one from
right here or anywhere
in 5 minutes.
Seriously,
5 minutes...
This is Banking Reimagined.
What's in your wallet?
Ok look, if you're not
the lead dog,
the scenery never changes.
That's why this is the view
for every other full-size
pickup.
And this year,
it's déjà vu all over again
'Cuz only the Ford F-150 with
its high strength,
military-grade
aluminum alloy body
gives you best-in-class torque,
best-in-class payload...
and you got it, baby...
best-in-class towing.
Still leading the pack.
This is the big dog!
This is the Ford F-150.
It doesn't just
raise the bar, pal.
It is the bar.
Colon cancer screening
for people
50 and older at average risk.
I think it's time
for a new screen.
For a different
kind of screen...
for colon cancer.
Thought about it?
His wife asked
about screening options
and her doctor
ordered me.
I'm Cologuard,
the noninvasive
test you use at home.
No special drink.
Just a trip
to the bathroom!
Cologuard.
Colon cancer screening
that's as easy as get,
go, gone.
Cologuard is not
right for everyone,
so ask your doctor if
it's right for you.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, AMERICA
STRONG.
CELEBRATING LEGENDARY HALL OF
FAMER FRANK ROBINSON, MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL'S FIRST
AFRICAN-AMERICAN MANAGER, AND
ONE OF THE GAME'S GREATEST
STARS.
>> LINE DRIVE TO LEFT FIELD.
WAY BACK -- IT IS GONE!
>> PROBABLY ONE OF THE TOP FIVE
TOUGHEST PLAYERS THAT I'VE EVER
BEEN AROUND.
THIS GUY WAS NOT ONLY A GREAT
PLAYER, HE WAS A HARD PLAYER,
BOY.
HE WAS AS TOUGH AS NAILS.
>> Reporter: FRANK ROBINSON WAS
ONE OF BASEBALL'S MOST
CELEBRATED AND MOST
INTIMIDATING HITTERS.
STARTING WITH THE REDS IN 1956,
HE WAS ROOKIE OF THE YEAR.
>> HE WAS THE BEST THAT I HAVE
EVER SEEN AT KNOWING WHAT THE
PITCHER WAS THROWING.
FRANK COULD TAKE HIS HAT OFF,
PUT IT IN FRONT OF HIS FACE AND
LOOK THROUGH ONE OF THOSE LITTLE
HOLES IN HIS HAT AND I ASKED HIM
ONE TIME, WHAT YOU ARE DOING?
AND HE SAID, I'M WATCHING THE
PITCHER.
>> Reporter: THEN ROBINSON'S
FIRST YEAR WITH THE ORIOLES,
1966, WOULD HELP CEMENT HIS
PLACE AS ONE OF THE GREATEST
BASEBALL PLAYERS OF ALL TIME.
HE WON BASEBALL'S TRIPLE CROWN,
LEADING THE LEAGUE WITH
49 HOMERS.
EARNING THE AMERICAN LEAGUE MVP
AWARD AND LEADING THE ORIOLES TO
THEIR FIRST WORLD SERIES TITLE.
>> ROBINSON, THE RIGHT-HAND
BATTER.
LONG DRIVE TO LEFT FIELD.
WAY BACK, WAY BACK.
KISS IT GOODBYE.
HOMERUN.
>> Reporter: HE WOULD LATER MAKE
HISTORY AS A MANAGER.
NO AFRICAN-AMERICAN HAD EVER
MANAGED IN THE MAJOR LEAGUES.
LEADING THE CLEVELAND INDIANS
STARTING IN 1975.
>> EVERYWHERE I WENT IT WAS,
HOW'S IT FEEL TO BE THE FIRST
BLACK MANAGER?
I JUST WANTED TO BE LOOKED UP ON
AND THOUGHT OF AS A MAJOR LEAGUE
MANAGER.
PEOPLE MADE SACRIFICES FOR ME,
COMING ALONG, SO, I WANTED TO
GIVE SOMETHING BACK AND THE DAY
THAT I FEEL LIKE I HAVE NOTHING
TO GIVE, OR NOTHING TO OFFER
BASEBALL, THAT'S WHEN I WILL
THEN FADE OFF INTO THE SUNSET.
>> A TRUE LEGEND.
ROBINSON WAS 83.
OUR THANKS TO ESPN AS WE LOOK
BACK TODAY.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
GOOD NIGHT.
NIGHT.
Everyone's got to listen to mom.
When it comes to reducing the
sugar in your family's diet,
Coke, Dr Pepper and Pepsi hear
you.
We're working together to do
just that.
Bringing you more great tasting
beverages with less sugar
or no sugar at all.
Smaller portion sizes,
clear calorie labels and
reminders to think balance.
Because we know mom wants what's
best.
More beverage choices, smaller
portions, less sugar.
BalanceUS.org
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]