>>> TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS.
THE VERDICT JUST IN.
THE DECORATED NAVY S.E.A.L.
ACCUSED OF MURDERING A WOUNDED
PRISONER IN IRAQ.
THE STUNNING MOMENT WHEN ANOTHER
S.E.A.L. TEAM MEMBER.
>>> AS BREAKING, THE EXPLOSION
IN AN AMERICAN NEIGHBOR.
FIREFIGHTERS LOOKING FOR
POSSIBLE VICTIMS.
THE MAN CALLING 911, SAYING HE'S
TRAPPED UNDER THE DEBRIS.
>>> THE NAIL-BITER WORLD CUP
VICTORY.
TEAM USA BEATING ENGLAND, THEIR
STAR PLAYER ON THE SIDELINES,
HURT.
SO, WILL SHE BE THERE FOR THE
FINALS?
>>> A SCATHING NEW GOVERNMENT
REPORT ABOUT LIFE INSIDE THOSE
MIGRANT DETENTION CENTERS.
MEN KEPT FOR A WEEK IN STANDING
ROOM ONLY CELLS.
ONE MANAGER CALLING THE SCENE A
TICKING TIME BOMB.
WHAT HOMELAND SECURITY IS NOW
SAYING.
>>> GROWING BACKLASH OVER
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S FOURTH OF JULY
PLANS.
TANKS AND FIGHTER JETS HEADED TO
THE NATIONAL MALL.
THE PRESIDENT ACCUSED OF TURNING
THE HOLIDAY INTO A POLITICAL
RALLY.
>>> THE MYSTERY OVER THE SUDDEN
DEATH OF ANGELS PITCHER TYLER
SKAGGS, FOUND DEAD IN HIS HOTEL
ROOM IN THE PRIME OF HIS CAREER.
WHAT AUTHORITIES AND THE TEAM
REVEALED TODAY.
>>> AND THE SHARK SCARE OFF THE
COAST.
A MOTHER AND HER CHILDREN IN THE
WATER WITH NO IDEA WHAT'S
LURKING JUST A FEW FEET AWAY.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH
US ON THIS BUSY TUESDAY NIGHT.
I'M CECILIA VEGA, IN FOR DAVID.
AND WE BEGIN WITH THAT BOMB
SHELL VERDICT IN THE TRIAL OF A
FORMER NAVY S.E.A.L.
SPECIAL OPERATIONS CHIEF EDWARD
GALLAGHER FOUND NOT GUILTY.
HE WAS CONVICTED OF A SINGLE
CRIME, TAKING A PHOTO WITH A
BODY OF A DEAD CAPTIVE.
GALLAGHER WAS DEPLOYED TO IRAQ
IN 2017 WHEN THE INCIDENT TOOK
PLACE.
HIS OWN PLATOON TURNING HIM IN.
BUT THEN, THAT STUNNING TURN
DURING THE TRIAL.
A PROSECUTION WITNESS TESTIFYING
THAT HE, NOT GALLAGHER, ACTUALLY
KILLED THE CAPTIVE.
ABC'S CLAYTON SANDELL STARTS US
OFF.
>> Reporter: EDWARD GALLAGHER'S
ATTORNEYS CELEBRATING ON THE
STEPS OF THE COURTHOUSE TONIGHT,
AFTER A MILITARY JURY FOUND THE
DECORATED NAVY S.E.A.L. NOT
GUILTY OF PREMEDITATED MURDER.
>> HUGE VICTORY.
HUGE WEIGHT OFF THE GALLAGHERS.
HUGE VICTORY FOR JUSTICE.
>> Reporter: THE 19-YEAR COMBAT
VETERAN WAS ACCUSED OF WAR
CRIMES DURING A 2017 TOUR IN
IRAQ, INCLUDING MURDERING THIS
TEENAGE ISIS PRISONER, SEEN
WOUNDED IN THIS IRAQI TV VIDEO.
FELLOW S.E.A.L. COREY SCOTT,
GRANTED IMMUNITY, TESTIFIED THAT
HE SAW GALLAGHER, A MEDIC, STAB
THAT TEEN IN THE NECK.
BUT IN A SHOCKING TWIST, SCOTT
TESTIFIED THAT HE, NOT
GALLAGHER, KILLED THE BETTEEN BY
PLUGGING HIS AIRWAY TO PREVENT
HIM FROM BEING TORTURED BY IRAQI
FORCES, SAYING, "I KNEW HE WAS
GOING TO DIE ANYWAY."
GALLAGHER'S DEFENSE TEAM ARGUED
DURING THE TWO-WEEK TRIAL THAT
THE CASE WAS BUILT ON FALSE
ACCUSATIONS FROM DISGRUNTLED
SAILORS.
>> THIS IS NOT A MURDER, THIS IS
A MUTINY.
THIS IS A GROUP OF YOUNG
DISGRUNTLED SAILORS THAT DIDN'T
LIKE BEING TOLD THAT THEY WERE
COWARDS.
AND SO THEY DECIDED TO CONSPIRE
TO TAKE DOWN THE CHIEF.
>> AND CLAYTON SANDELL JOINS US
NOW LIVE.
CLAYTON, WE KNOW THAT EDWARD
GALLAGHER WAS CONVICTED OF THAT
ONE CHARGE, POSING FOR A PICTURE
OF A CAPTIVE'S DEAD BODY.
SO, COULD HE STILL FACE PRISON
TIME?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
CECILIA.
PROSECUTORS SHOWED THOSE
PICTURES DURING THE TRIAL.
DEFENSE ATTORNEYS ARGUE THAT THE
SENTENCE FOR THAT CRIME WOULD BE
LESS THAN THE TIME HE'S ALREADY
SERVED, SO THEY BELIEVE
GALLAGHER WILL BE GOING HOME
TONIGHT.
CECILIA?
>> CLAYTON, THANK YOU.
>>> TO OUR OTHER TOP STORY
TONIGHT, THAT MASSIVE EXPLOSION
ROCKING AN ENTIRE NEIGHBORHOOD
IN NORTH CAROLINA.
THE STUNNING IMAGE FROM ABOVE.
A HOLE WHERE A HOME USED TO BE.
FIRST RESPONDERS COMBING THROUGH
THE RUBBLE.
ONE MAN TRAPPED UNDERNEATH,
USING HIS CELL PHONE TO CALL FOR
HELP.