>> NOW ABC7 NEWS AT NOON.
ON YOUR SIDE.
WE BEGIN WITH A BREAKING NEWS
ALERT.
>>Adrianna: THAT BREAKING NEWS
COMING FROM THE WHITE HOUSE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP DECLARING A
NATIONAL EMERGENCY FOR HIS
BORDER WALL.
EVEN THOUGH CONGRESS PASSED A
BIPARTISAN BILL TO KEEP THE
GOVERNMENT OPEN AND PROVIDE
FUNDS FOR BORDER SECURITY.
THE MOVE, EVEN THE PRESIDENT OF
NOLOGY, WILL LIKELY DRAW OUT A
LONG TIME LEGAL WAR.
SERENA MARSHALL HAS THE
DETAILS.
>> UNABLE TO GET THE FUNDS THAT
HE WANTED, PRESIDENT TRUMP
GOING AT IT ALONE.
SIGNING THE BY PERSON FUNDING
BILL BUT ALSO DECLARING A
NATIONAL EMERGENCY.
>> IT IS A GREAT THING TO DO.
BECAUSE WE HAVE INVASION OF
DRUGS, INVASION OF GANGS AND
INVASION OF PEOPLE AND IS
UNACCEPTABLE.
>> WITH THIS MOVE THE PRESENT
IS SECURING NEARLY $8 BILLION
FOR HIS BORDER WALL.
NEARLY $1.4 BILLION FROM THE
BORDER SECURITY BILL WITH THE
EMERGENCY DECLARATION ANOTHER
THREE AND HALF BILLION FROM THE
PENTAGON CONSTRUCTION BUDGET.
THE REMAINING FUNDS THROUGH
EXECUTIVE ORDERS INCLUDING $600
BILLION FROM THE TREASURY
DEPARTMENT AND AN ADDITIONAL 2
AND A HALF BILLION DOLLARS FROM
THE PENTAGON.
THE DECLARATION, NOT ENTIRELY
UNEXPECTED.
DURING THE 35 DAY SHUTDOWN, THE
PRESIDENT HAD SAID.> PEOPLE
EITHER HAVE A WIN OR I WILL
DECLARE ANATIONAL EMERGENCY.
> IT IS COMMENTS LIKE THAT
THAT HAVE DEMOCRATS CALLING THE
MOVE A LAWLESS ACT IN .
>> USING THIS TO MEET A
CAMPAIGN PROMISE IS SIMPLY A
TERRIBLE IDEA.
>> AS A CITIZEN, DONALD TRUMP
CRITICIZED PRESIDENT OBAMA FOR
TAKING EXECUTIVE ACTION FIVE
YEARS AGO FOR THE DREAMERS.
TO THINK THAT POLICE MUST NOT
LET PRESIDENT OBAMA SUBVERT THE
CONSTITUTION FOR HIS OWN USE.
BEFORE THE SPEAKER EVEN SAID
THE BILL TO THE PRESIDENT SHE
OFFERED A WARNING.
>> WE WILL NOT HAVE AN END RUN
AROUND THE CONGRESS OF THE
UNITED STATES.
>> FOLLOWING THE PRESIDENT'S
REMARKS, THEY ISSUED A JOINT
STATEMENT SAYING THE
PRESIDENT'S ACTIONS CLEARLY
VIOLATE THE CONSTITUTION AND IF
UNCHECKED WILL FUNDAMENTALLY
CHECK OF THE ALTAR BALANCE OF
POWER.
>>Adrianna: TO SEE MORE OF THE
PRESIDENT'S COMMENTS TODAY AND
TO FOLLOW ALL THE DEVELOPERS
WITH THE BORDER WALL, DOWNLOAD
THE ABC7 NEWS APP.
>>> JUSTICE RUTH BADER GINSBURG
IS BACK IN THE SUPREME COURT
FOR THE FIRST TIME SINCE CANCER
SURGERY LEISURE.
THE COURT IS THE 85-YEAR-OLD
JUSTICE IS PARTICIPATING.
SHE HAD TWO CANCERS NOTICE FROM
HER LEFT LUNG REMOVED IN
DECEMBER AND NOW SHE IS CANCER
FREE.>>> A BEAUTIFUL WEATHER
DAY TO GET OUTSIDE FOR A LUNCH.
STEVE RUDIN IS HERE FOR A CHECK
OF THE FORECAST AND HOW WARM IT
WILL GO BEFORE THE TEMPERATURES
DROP TOMORROW.
>>Steve: LOOKING AT A NICE
AFTERNOON SHAPING UP WITH A
GOOD AMOUNT OF SUNSHINE.
THIS IS OUR BRAND-NEW VIEW FROM
TOP THE WATERGATE HOTEL LOOKING
AT THE POTOMAC RIVER.
WE HAVE GEORGETOWN RIGHT OVER
HERE AND ON THE OTHER SIDE OF
THE BRIDGE IS ROSLYN.
A NICE AFTERNOON IF YOU ARE
GOING TO BE OUT AND ABOUT.
TEMPERATURE ALREADY IN THE
LOWER 60S AT REAGAN NATIONAL
AIRPORT, MID-60S IN LEESBURG,
57 DEGREES RIGHT NOW IN
WINCHESTER.
I DO WANT TO SHOW YOU STORM
WATCH 7 SATELLITE AND RADAR
WITH CLOUD COVER OFF TO THE
WEST OF US AND IT WILL
EVENTUALLY MAKE ITS WAY TO OUR
AREA LATER THIS AFTERNOON.
FORECAST FOR TODAY, IT DOES NOT
GET MUCH BETTER THAN THIS FOR
THE MIDDLE OF FEBRUARY.
WE ARE CALLING FOR A DAYTIME HI
IN THE MIDDLE 60S WITH ADDED
AFTERNOON CLOUDS WITH COMING UP
IN A FEW MINUTES I AM TRACKING
OUR NEXT WEATHER MAKER THAT
MIGHT BRING A LITTLE BIT OF
WINTRY WEATHER TO PARTS OF THE
DMV.
I WILL TELL YOU EXACTLY WHERE,
GIVE YOU THE TIMING AND LOOK
AHEAD TO PRESIDENT'S DAY IN
JUST A FEW MINUTES.
>Adrianna: VICE PRESIDENT
MIKE PENCE HEADED TO MUNICH,
GERMANY AFTER MAKING HIS FIRST
VISIT TO AUSCHWITZ.
IT WAS A CONCENTRATION CAMP
OCCUPIED IN POLAND DURING WORLD
WAR II.
HE PAID TRIBUTE AFTER HE.
>> THERE IS A DEEPLY DISTURBING
TREND.
ANOTHER CHILD IS THE VICTIM OF
GUN VIOLENCE.
THIS TIME IT IS A 12-YEAR-OLD
BOY HIT BY A STRAY BULLET IN A
SHOOTOUT ON POND STREET IN
NORTHEAST.
POLICE CHIEF PETER NEWSOM
CALLING FOR A STOP TO THE
SENSELESS VIOLENCE.EANWHILE
THE SEARCH IS ON FOR THE
SHOOTER AND JOHN RESULTS IS
FOLLOWING THE INVESTIGATION FOR
US.
>>John: THAT IS RIGHT.
THIS BOY IS FIGHTING FOR HIS
LIFE AT THIS HOUR AND NOT A
GOOD TREND.
THE THIRD CHILD TO BE STRUCK BY
A STRAY BULLET IN D.C. SO FAR
THIS YEAR.
WHEN D.C. POLICE AND PARENTS
ARRIVED HERE IN NORTHEAST
YESTERDAY, THEY FOUND THE
12-YEAR-OLD BOY AND RESPONSIVE
OUTSIDE HERE NEAR HIS HOME.
OU CAN SEE AT THIS HOUR,
POLICE STILL HAVE POND STREET
CLOSED OFF.
THIS IS CLOSE TO THE KENILWORTH
RECREATION CENTER AND POOL WITH
THE POLICE CHIEF MAKING IT VERY
CLEAR THAT THIS WAS NOT A
SINGLE GUN INCIDENT.
THERE WERE MULTIPLE PUPPIES OUT
HERE LAST NIGHT.
HE IS NOT SURE IF THERE WAS AN
EXCHANGE OF GUNFIRE BUT BULLETS
DEFINITELY CAME FROM DIFFERENT
GUNS AND OUR VIDEO INDICATES
THAT OUR CAMERA CAPTURING 48
EVIDENCE MARKERS AND MOST OF
THOSE WERE SHELL CASINGS.T
LEAST ONE CAR WINDOW WAS BLOWN
OUT.
THE POINT WAS RUSHED TO THE
HOSPITAL IN CRITICAL CONDITION
AT THIS HOUR.
>> WE HAD A LITTLE KID, LITTLE
BABY OVER AT THE BUS STOP AND
WE HAD A SIX-YEAR-OLD THE OTHER
NIGHT WHO WAS IN THE BACKSEAT
OF A CAR THE 2400 BLOCK OF
ALABAMA AND NOW WE HAVE A
12-YEAR-OLD KID WHO SHOULD BE
OUT OR AT HOME ENJOYING HIS
EVENING.
HE IS AT ONE OF OUR LOCAL
HOSPITAL STRUGGLING BECAUSE HE
HAS BEEN SHOT.
IT HAS GOT TO STOP.>John:
NEIGHBOR STILL ABC7 NEWS THAT
THEY ALSO HEARD GUNSHOTS AROUND
THE SAME TIME THE NIGHT BEFORE.
WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
AUTHORITIES ARE ASKING FOR THE
PUBLIC TO BE ON THE LOOKOUT FOR
A SILVER VEHICLE WITH AT LEAST
FOUR PEOPLE INSIDE.
POLICE SAY ONE PERSON WEARING
AN ORANGE TREE HERE LAST NIGHT.
IN NORTHEAST WASHINGTON JOHN
RESULTS ABC7 NEWS.
>>Adrianna: THE FIRST OF FOUR
DAMASCUS HIGH SCHOOL JUNIOR
VARSITY PLAYERS ACCUSED OF
RAPING TEAMMATES WITH A
BROOMSTICK, FACING A JUDGE
TODAY.
THE 15 OR ASKING FOR HIS CASE
TO BE TRIED IN JUVENILE COURT.
HIS THREE CODEFENDANTS WILL
HAVE SIMILAR HEARINGS IN THE
COMING WEEKS.
>>> THIS WEEK WE REPORTED ON A
FIGHT INSIDE THE HIGH SCHOOL
AND A STUDENT IS STILL IN THE
HOSPITAL WITH A FRACTURED
SCHOOL AND A BLOOD CLOT WITH
ABC SEVEN LEARNING PROTOCOLS
FROM THE SCHOOL TO REPORT TO
NOT WHEN ONE WERE NOT FOLLOWED
IN THIS CASE BUT IT WAS THE
STUDENTS FATHER WHO CALLED
9-1-1. WE HAVE ASKED FOR
INTERVIEWS WITH THE
SUPERINTENDENT AS WELL AS
McGRUDER'S PRINCIPAL AND BOTH
HAVE SAID THAT THEY ARE
UNAVAILABLE.
>>> COMING UP NEXT AT NOON.
KIDS ARE SUPPOSED BE ON THEIR
BEST BEHAVIOR AND STRENGTH THAT
ALSO APPLY TO PARENTS?
ONE WOULD THINK.
LOOKING BACK MORE ON THIS
WRESTLING MATCH MELEE THAT
HAPPENED OFF THE MATCH AND SEND
THESE PARENTS TO TIMEOUT.
PLUS GETTING A GIFT WRONG, IT
SOMETIMES HAPPENS.
BUT WHEN SOMEONE TELLS YOU WHAT
THEY WANT IS TO GET IT WRONG,
BACK TO BE A BIG PROBLEM.
MISTAKE THAT TURNED A WOMAN'S
VALENTINE'S DAY VERY SOUR.
>>Eric: ON THE ROADWAYS HIS
FRIDAY AFTERNOON WE HAVE A FEW
SLOW SPOTS TO WORRY ABOUT
STARTING OFF ON 66 NEAR FAIRFAX
COUNTY PARKWAY, BOTH DIRECTIONS
SEEM TO BE OPEN FROM EARLIER
WORK ZONES AT THIS POINT.
LITTLE BIT OF VOLUME TO CONTEND
WITH AT THIS TIME.
FOR THE MOST PART TRAFFIC IS
MOVING.
CAPITAL BELTWAY INNER LOOP
HEADING OUT OF SPRINGFIELD AND
LOOKS LIKE ANOTHER MOBILE
BROOKSTONE HERE.
A BIT OF A SUDDEN JAM HEADING
UP THIS WAY OUT OF SPRINGFIELD.
SOUTHBOUND 95 WILL BEGIN TO
SLOW DOWN ALREADY FROM MORNING
OVER THE UPPER POND OVER THE
BRIDGE.
THEY HAVE A WORK ZONE PAST ROOT
FOR INTO FT. SILL BLOCKING THE
LEFT LANE INTO ALLENTOWN ROAD.
IT DOES SLOW THINGS DOWN BACK
TO
>>Adrianna: THIS WAS CAUGHT ON
CAMERA AND YOU SEE HERE PARENTS
FIGHTING DURING THEIR
CHILDREN'S WRESTLING MATCH.
THIS HAPPENED IN WISCONSIN.
THINGS GOT UGLY FAST.
YOU CAN SEE A WOMAN DRESSED IN
A BLACK SHIRT IN A HEATED
EXCHANGE WITH ANOTHER MOM.
THEN A MAN GETS UP INTO HER
FACE AND HOW TO GET PULLED AWAY
BY SEVERAL OTHER PARENTS.
THEN THE TWO WOMEN SCUFFLING
THEY FALL TO THE GROUND ALL
BALL THE KIDS ARE STILL
COMPETING ON THE MAP.
ALL OF THESE PARENTS WERE ALL
THREE INVOLVED WERE CITED FOR
DISORDERLY CONDUCT.>> FOR
THE FIRST TIME SINCE BEING
RELEASED FROM AN IMMIGRATION
RETENTION CENTER, ROBERT 21
SAVAGE ADDRESSING HIS ARREST ON
CAMERA.
THE 26-YEAR-OLD BORN IN ENGLAND
CAME TO THE U.S. AT SEVEN YEARS
OLD.
HE WAS RAISED IN ATLANTA BUT IS
LIVING HERE ON AN EXPIRED VISA.
HERE IS WHAT HE HAD TO SAY TO
ABC'S LINDSAY DAVIS.
>> AT A CERTAIN POINT, 2006
YOUR VISA EXPIRED.
>> I DO NOT KNOW WHAT HE VISA
WAS.
I WAS SEVEN WHEN I FIRST CAME
HERE.
AND YOU I WAS NOT BORN HERE,
BUT I DO NOT KNOW WHAT, WHAT
THAT MEANT AS FAR AS WHEN I
TRANSITIONED INTO AN ADULT HOW
IT WOULD AFFECT MY LIFE.
I WAS NOT HIDING IT, BUT IT WAS
LIKE I DO NOT WANT TO GET
DEPORTED SO NOT COME OUT AND
SAY, I WAS NOT BORN HERE.
I HAVE BEEN HERE 20 YEARS, 19
YEARS.
THIS IS ALL I KNOW.OU KNOW
WHAT I AM SAYING?
I DO NOT FEEL LIKE YOU SHOULD
BE ARRESTED AND PUT IN A PLACE
WHERE A MURDER WOULD BE FOR
JUST BEING IN THE COUNTRY.
FOR TOO LONG.
>> THE ROBBERS REPRESENTATIVES
SAY THEY ARE IN THE PROCESS OF
SECURING HIS IMMIGRATION STATUS
TO MAKE HIM A CITIZEN.
GOING FORWARD, HE SAYS HE WILL
DEVOTE TIME TO BRING AWARENESS
TO IMMIGRATION ISSUES.>>
POLICE IN CHICAGO SAY TWO MEN
QUESTION IN THE PORTAGE ATTACK
ON JUSSIE SMOLLETT ARE INDEED
SUSPECTS.
ONE OF THE MEN HAS A CONNECTION
TO THE SHOW.
>> AUTHORITIES IN CHICAGO
BELIEVE THEY FOUND TWO
POTENTIAL SUSPECTS SEEN HERE ON
THE SURVEILLANCE IMAGE FROM THE
NIGHT OF THE ALLEGED ATTACK ON
JUSSIE SMOLLETT.> HAVE YOU
SEEN THAT IMAGE AND DID YOU
BELIEVE THAT THEY COULD
POSSIBLY BE THE ATTACKERS,
>> I DO NOT HAVE ANY DOUBT IN
MY MIND.
THAT IS THAT IS THEM.
NEVER DID.
>> THE TREATMENT WERE PICKED UP
FOR QUESTIONING AT THE AIRPORT
ON WEDNESDAY.
AS THE NETWORK TURNED ON A
FLIGHT FROM NIGERIA.
WHAT AN ACTOR WHO HAS APPEARED
ON JUSSIE SMOLLETT SHOW,
EMPIRE.
POLICE RAIDED THEIR HOMES,
TAKING SHOES, ELECTRONIC
DEVICES AND OTHER ITEMS POLICE
BELIEVE COULD BE KEY TO THE
INVESTIGATION.
THIS POINT, PLEASE DO ABC NEWS
THAT THEY ARE INVESTIGATING
WHETHER THE TWO INDIVIDUALS
COMMITTED THE ATTACK OR WHETHER
THE ATTACK HAPPENED AT ALL.
INVESTIGATORS SPENT PART OF
THURSDAY IS GETTING JUSSIE
SMOLLETT ABOUT THE INCIDENT.
THE ACTOR INSISTS HE IS TELLING
THE TRUTH.
>> WHO WOULD MAKE SOMETHING
LIKE THIS UP OR ADD SOMETHING
TO IT OR WHATEVER, IT MAYBE. I
CANNOT EVEN, I AM AN ADVOCATE,
I RESPECT TOO MUCH, THE PEOPLE
WHO I AM NOW ONE OF THOSE
PEOPLE, WHO HAS BEEN ATTACKED
IN ANY WAY.
YOU DO SUCH A DISSERVICE WHEN
YOU A LOT ABOUT THINGS LIKE
THIS.
>> IN A STATEMENT, 21ST CENTURY
FOLKS SAY THEY CONTINUE TO
STAND BEHIND JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
SO FAR, NO CHARGES HAVE BEEN
FILED AGAINST THE TWO POTENTIAL
SUSPECTS.AGGIE RULLI ABC
NEWS NEAR.
>>Adrianna: A COUPLE IN
KENTUCKY IS LAUGHING TODAY
ABOUT A VALENTINE'S DAY MIXER.
ALAN HARRIS ASKED HIS WIFE NINA
WHAT SHE WANTED FOR VALENTINE'S
DAY AND SHE SAID SHE WANTED
TULIPS.
HE MISSED UNDERSTOOD AND HE
HEARD TURNIPS.
SO HE WENT OUT AND GOT HER SOME
TURNIPS AND HE MADE THEM AS
ROMANTIC AS POSSIBLE.
>> I WENT AND GOT THE BOOK AND
PUT THE TURNIPS IN THE BUCKET
THAT SAID I LOVE YOU ON IT I
GOT HER COFFEE AND HE COULD GO.
>> WHEN I GOT UP AND HAD MY
FIRST CUP OF COFFEE, HE SAID
OH, A TURNIPS ARE HERE.
AND I SAID TURNIPS?
>>Adrianna: WHEN ALAN REALIZED
HE MADE A MISTAKE, HE QUICKLY
WENT TO THE STORE AND BOUGHT
HER SOME TULIPS AND A BALLOON.
SHE DOES APPRECIATE HIS EFFORT
AND SAID THIS FANTASY HAS BEEN
SPECIAL IN MANY WAYS.
>>Steve: THAT IS REALLY NICE.
>>Adrianna: IT IS NOT A BAD
STORY BUT HE THOUGHT HE HEARD
SOMETHING AND HE GOT HER A
VALENTINE'S DAY GIFT, HE JUST
MISUNDERSTOOD.
>>Steve: WHAT DO YOU EVEN DO
TURNIPS?
DO YOU MAKE A SOUP OR DO YOU
ROAST THEM?
>>Adrianna: I DO NOT KNOW.
>>Steve: GIVE THEM AS
VALENTINE'S DAY GIFTS INSTEAD
OF TULIPS.
IN A STORY WITH A NICE ENDING.
>> TODAY, WOW.
WHAT AN ABSOLUTE GORGEOUS
AFTERNOON.HIS IS OUR
BRAND-NEW CAMERA ATOP THE
WATERGATE HOTEL IN NORTHWEST
D.C.. NOW WE HAVE IT TURNED
TOWARDS GEORGETOWN UNIVERSITY.
THIS CAMERA CAN SEE EVERYTHING
FROM THE RIVER TO ROSSLYN OVER
TOWARD THE KENNEDY CENTER AND
THE AIR FORCE MEMORIAL DURING
THE NEXT HOUR I WILL GIVE YOU A
TOUR OF ALL THE GREAT SHOTS
THAT WE HAVE.
HEREIS OUR VANTAGE POINT OVER
NATIONAL HARBOR WITH A FEW
CLOUDS OUT THERE RIGHT NOW.
OTHERWISE IT IS QUITE, IT IS
DRY AND IS VERY MILD .
OVERLOOKING THE TIDAL BAIN,
NICE AFTERNOON AND I HOPE YOU
HAVE THE CHANCE TO GET OUT
THERE AND ENJOY IT.LOOK AT
THESE TEMPERATURES.
MY GOODNESS PAID FOR THE MIDDLE
OF FEBRUARY WE ARE IN THE
MIDDLE 60S OVER AT LEESBURG.
63 IN GAITHERSBURG, SAME IN
FREDERICK AND NOW 61 AT
ANDREWS, ANNAPOLIS AT 64.
THIS A LITTLE COOLER OFF TOWARD
THE NORTH AND WEST OF US.
CUMBERLAND, MARYLAND REPORTING
IN A CHILLY 42 DEGREES.
CHECK OF THE WINDS AND IS A
LITTLE BIT BREEZY UP THERE WITH
15 TO 20 MILE-PER-HOUR WINDS.
THE TEMPERATURE CHANGE.
ESTERDAY AT THIS TIME, AROUND
15 TO 22 DEGREES WARMER.
IT WILL NOT LAST LONG.
WE HAVE A COLD FRONT ON THE WAY
LATER THIS AFTERNOON INTO THE
EVENING HOURS BUT THAT WILL
CHANGE OUR AIR MASS FOR THE
UPCOMING WEEKEND.
IN THE MEANTIME, WE ARE BASKING
IN A GOOD AMOUNT OF SUNSHINE OR
BRIGHT SKIES, SHOULD SAY WITH
ADDED CAUSE UP TO THE WEST OF
US.
YOU MIGHT SEE A STRAY SPRINKLE
OR TWO BUT IT WILL NOT AMOUNT
TO WHOLE LOT.
YOU WILL GOING TO BE OUT AND
ABOUT WJLA 24/7 TIME HOUR,
TEMPERATURES IN THE 60S WITH A
LIGHT JACKET IS ALL YOU WILL
NEED.
LATER ON THIS EVENING THE
TEMPERATURES BEGIN TO SLIDE,
MAYBE CHECKING OUT A MOVIE OR
WALKING ON 14TH STREET OR
GEORGETOWN OR WHEREVER YOU
MAYBE GOING.
WE ARE LOOKING AT ADDED CLOUD
COVER.
FOR TONIGHT, IT WILL BE COLD UP
THERE 20 TO 38 DEGREES AND THAT
IS TEMPERATURES BUT UNDER
MOSTLY CLOUDY SKIES.
IT WILL BE A CHILLY START YOUR
DAY TOMORROW.
ALSO, SOME OF YOU MIGHT BE
LOOKING AT A LITTLE BIT OF A
WINTRY MIX.
HOUR BY HOUR FOR TOMORROW AND
WE WILL CALL FOR MOSTLY CLOUDY
SKIES WITH A CHANCE FOR A
LITTLE BIT OF SLEEP MIXING IN
WITH RAIN AND SNOW AND AS WE
HEAD TO THE FIRST PART OF THE
DAY, BUT THEN WE SHOULD SEE A
GOOD AMOUNT OF CLEARING DURING
THE AFTERNOON HOURS.
TEMPERATURES THAT WILL MAKE IT
INTO THE 40S BUT HERE IS OUR
FUTURECAST 90 WANT TO START WE
ARE RIGHT NOW.
IT IS DRY UP THERE, OBVIOUSLY.
AS YOU MOVE THROUGH THE EVENING
HOURS WE DO STAY MAINLY DRY.
THEN, LATER ON TONIGHT IN EARLY
TOMORROW MORNING WE HAVE A
SYSTEM THAT IS GOING TO MOVE
JUST TO THE SOUTH OF THE D.C.
METRO AREA.
BRICK YOU SEE THE AREA SHADED
IN BLUE, IT MAY SEE A SLUSHY
ACCUMULATION ON GRASSY AREAS.
THIS INCLUDES THE DISTRICT AND
ARLINGTON AND ALEXANDRIA BUT
FOR AS QUICKLY AS IT ARRIVES,
THAT IS HOW FAST IT IS OUT OF
FEAR.
BY NOONTIME TOMORROW OUR SKIES
BEGIN TO CLEAR AND GARRETT,
ALLEGHENY AND WASHINGTON
COUNTIES AND QUESTION MARYLAND
WITH A LOT OF SUNSHINE.
LATER TOMORROW AFTERNOONAT 5:00
WE WILL DEAL WITH A NICE SUNSET
AROUND THE DMV AS THE COOLER
AIR OVEREXPOSE THE REGION.
HOW MUCH THE ARE WE TALKING
ABOUT?
LESS THAN AN INCH , IF EVEN
THAT.
ONCE AGAIN SOUTH OF THE D.C.
METRO AREA AND WE ARE TALKING
ABOUT OVER TOWARD
FREDERICKSBURG AND CULPEPER.
ONCE AGAIN, MAINLY ON GRASSY
AREAS AND WE ARE NOT GOING TO
SEE A WHOLE LOT OTHER THAN A
NUISANCE IN TERMS OF THE
WEATHER.
HERE IS OUR FORECAST.
THIS IS A LITTLE BIT OF
ADJUSTING HERE.
WE ARE LOOKING TEMPERATURES IN
THE 40S TOMORROW AND WE STAY IN
THE 40S AND NEXT WEEK.
EVEN THE 30S BEFORE WE FINALLY
START TO WARM THINGS UP JUST A
LITTLE BIT.
ONCE AGAIN, TOMORROW YOU ARE
DRIVING DO NOT EXPECT TO SEE A
BIG PROBLEM.
HOWEVER, WHAT ROADWAYS AROUND
HERE TO SLOW THINGS DOWN BUT
THANKFULLY THE TIME IS WORKING
TO OUR ADVANTAGE.
IT IS A WEEKEND MORNING, EARLY
ON AND TOMORROW NIGHT LOOKING
GOOD.
>>Adrianna: THANK YOU STEVE.
COMING UP ON ABC7 NEWS AT NOON.
You might take something
for your heart...
or joints.
But do you take something
for your brain.
With an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish,
Prevagen has been shown
in clinical trials
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>Adrianna: HAPPENING TONIGHT
20/20 WITH A NEW INSIDE OF THE
HORRIFYING KILLING SPREE OF TED
BUNDY 30 YEARS AFTER HIS
EXECUTION.
HE ADMITTED TO MURDERING AT
LEAST 30 WOMEN AND MANY OF THEM
HE KIDNAPPED AND SEXUALLY
ASSAULTED.DESPITE HIS
CONFESSION, AUTHORITIES DO
BELIEVE THERE MIGHT HAVE BEEN
MANY MORE VICTIMS.
ABC DEBORAH ROBERTS JOINS US
LIVE WITH A PREVIEW OF WHAT WE
WILL SEE TONIGHT.
IT IS ALWAYS GREAT TO HAVE YOU.
I WANT TO START BY ASKING YOU,
WHY ARE AMERICANS AND PEOPLE IN
GENERAL SO FASCINATED WITH TED
BUNDY?
>> THAT IS A VERY GOOD QUESTION
ANDWE WONDERED THE SAME THING.
MANY THINK ABOUT IT, SADLY, HE
HAD ALL THE ELEMENTS OF
FASCINATION.
HE WAS CHARMING, GOOD-LOOKING.
REMEMBER, HE EVEN REPRESENT
HIMSELF AS HIS OWN LAWYER IN
HIS TRIAL.
THIS WAS A GUY WHO, NOT ONLY ,
TRICKED A LOT OF WOMEN AND LED
THEM TO THEIR DEATH BUT WAS
ABLE TO CHARM HIS JAILERS,
CHARM, BASICALLY COURTHOUSE
WORKERS IN AUTHORITIES.
NOBODY THOUGHT THIS WAS THE
KIND OF GUY WHO WAS THE PICTURE
IN FACE OF HORRIBLE CRIME AND
LET ALONE, A SERIAL KILLER.
I THINK BECAUSE HE WAS SUCH A
SMOOTH OPERATOR AND EVEN TO THE
VERY END, INVESTIGATORS WANTED
TO TALK WITH THEM.
HE BEGAN TO TALK ABOUT HIS
CRIMES AT THE VERY END BEFORE
HE WAS EXECUTED.
PEOPLE WANTED TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT WENT ON INSIDE HIS MIND.
A MAN HE WAS SEEMINGLY SO
NORMAL, HAD STUDIED PSYCHOLOGY
IN COLLEGE, HAD A LAW STUDENT,
HAD A GIRLFRIEND.
CUT THE PICTURE OF THE GUY NEXT
DOOR BUT HAD THE DARK SIDE AND
PRAYED ON WOMEN IN SUCH A
VICIOUS, VICIOUS AWFUL WAYS.
>>Adrianna: WE KNOW TOWARD THE
END OF HIS LIFE BEFORE HE WAS
EXECUTED, HE DID SIT DOWN AND
TALK WITH INVESTIGATORS.
THEY HAVE SAID THAT HE GAVE
THEM QUITE A BIT O INSIGHT ON
HOW SERIAL KILLERS WORK.
>> HE DID.
WHAT WAS INTERESTING WAS THAT
HE WAS STILL WHEELING AND
DEALING ALL THE WAY TO THE END.
HE WOULD WITHHOLD THE
INFORMATION AND HE KNEW THAT HE
COULD USE IT TO BUY A LITTLE
TIME, EVEN BEFORE HIS
EXECUTION.
THIS WAS A GUY WHO NEVER
STOPPED MANIPULATING, BUT HE
DID EVENTUALLY, AS YOU SAID,
START TO COME CLEAN ABOUT SOME
OF THE CRIMES THAT HE
COMMITTED.
TO SPELL A LITTLE BIT MORE TO
INVESTIGATORS.
TONIGHT ON A ONE, BESIDES JUST
THESE HORRIBLE CRIMES YOU WILL
HEAR FROM THE VICTIM'S
THEMSELVES.
SOME OF THEM THAT ESCAPED HIS
CLUTCHES IN FLORIDA THAT WERE
TRACKED BY HIM BUT MANAGED TO
GET AWAY.
YOU WILL HEAR FROM
INVESTIGATORS ABOUT WHAT THEY
LEARNED FROM HIM AND HOW THEY
WERE ABLE TO TRACK HIM DOWN.
ONE OF THE MOST NOTORIOUS
MODERN-DAY SERIAL KILLERS AND
ONE THAT PEOPLE STILL SEEM TO
BE TALKING ABOUT ALL THESE
DECADES LATER.
>>Adrianna: WOW.
THAT 20/20 IS A TWO HOUR EVENT
STARTING AT 9:00 TONIGHT.
GREAT TO HAVE YOU.
>>Adrianna: HOLLYWOOD ON THE
POTOMAC IS ALIVE AND WELL TODA
.
IF YOU ARE HEADED TO THE
NATIONAL MALL YOU COULD SEE
CAMERAS AND COSTUMES.
THE HULU HIT SHOW, THE
HANDMAID'S TALE IS FILMING.
WE ARE TOLD THEY WILL BE
SHOOTING UNTIL THE END OF THE
DAY.
>>> AT LEAST THEY HAD A NICE
DAY TO SHOOT.
>>Steve: ,VISIT D.C. AND YOU
NEVER KNOW WHAT YOU WILL SEE,
MAYBE A MOVIE CAKE.
>>> TODAY IS THE DAY TO GET
OUTSIDE AND GRAB A BITE TO EAT
OR MAYBE GOOD TO HEAR ROOF DECK
IF YOU HAVE ONE.
OR JUST THE FRONT PORCH SOUNDS
GOOD TO ME.
64, 65 DEGREES FOR THIS
AFTERNOON AND MUCH COLDER
TOMORROW WITH A WINTRY MIX.
MAINLY DURING THE MORNING HOURS
SOUTH OF D.C.. YOU MIGHT SEE
>> YOU ARE WATCHING ABC7 NEWS
AT NOON.
ON YOUR SIDE.
>>Adrianna: PRESIDENT TRUMP
SIGNING A FUNNY BILL TO PREVENT
ANOTHER PARTIAL GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN.
AND ALSO DECLARING A NATIONAL
EMERGENCY ON THE SOUTHERN
BORDER.
HIS ILLUSTRATION BELIEVES THAT
OCCLUSION ALLOWS YOU TO
REALLOCATE BILLIONS OF DOLLARS
FOR HIS BORDER WALL.
THE PRESIDENT DEFENDED HIS
DECISION DURING A NEWS
CONFERENCE IN THE ROSE GARDEN A
FEW MOMENTS AGO.
>> AND WE WILL HAVE A NATIONAL
EMERGENCY AND DID WE WILL BE
SUED AND THEY WILL SUE US IN
THE NINTH CIRCUIT.
EVEN THOUGH IT SHOULD NOT BE
THERE.
WE WILL POSSIBLY GET A BAD
RULING AND THEN WE WILL GET
ANOTHER BAD RULING AND THEN THE
PEOPLE END UP IN THE SUPREME
COURT AND THEN HOPEFULLY WE
WILL GET A FAIR SHAKE.
THEN WE WILL WIN AT THE SUPREME
COURT.
>>Adrianna: CONGRESS NOW HAS 15
DAYS TO PASS A RESOLUTION
DISAPPROVING OF THE
ECLARATION.G OF THE
A NUMBER OF REPUBLICANS ARE
LIKELY TO SUPPORT THE
RESOLUTION, SAYING THE
DECLARATION SETS A DANGEROUS
PRECEDENT.
>>> OF COURSE TO SEE MORE OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S COMMENTS
TODAY INTERVAL ALL DEVELOPMENTS
WITH THIS BOARDWALK, DOWNLOAD
THE ABC7 NEWS APP.
>>> AMAZON DELIVERED IN CRYSTAL
CITY BUT THE GIANT IS PULLING
OUT OF ITS NEW YORK CITY HQ2
SPOTTED SIDING MAJOR POLITICAL
OPPOSITION OVER THAT NEARLY $3
BILLION OF INCENTIVES PROMISED
TO THE COMPANY.
AMAZON IS STILL COMMITTED TO
VIRGINIA AND THE COMPANY CLAIMS
IT IS NOT LOOKING FOR A NEW
PLACE, BUT MARYLAND GOVERNOR,
LARRY HOGAN SAYS HIS
MINISTRATIONHAS HAD PULMONARY
DISCUSSIONS ABOUT EXPANSION IN
HIS DAY.
>>> A TRAFFIC ALERT FOR YOU.
CHRIS WILL BE INSTALLING THE .
DEMONSTRATE COURSE AT HOME TO
HIS BOSTON NEIGHBORHOOD AND
DISCLOSURES BEGIN AT 2:00 THIS
AFTERNOON AND THEY WENT 6:00
SUNDAY NIGHT.
FOR MUCH OF THE TIME WILSON
BOULEVARD WILL BE CLOSED
BETWEEN NORTH OAKLAND AND NORTH
TAYLOR STREETS.
SECTIONS OF POLISH, QUINCY,
RANDOLPH AND STEWART STREET
NEAR WILSON BOULEVARD WILL ALSO
BE CLOSED.
MOTORS ARE URGED TO USE NORTH
LEE ROAD AND FAIRFAX DRIVE TO
BYPASS THE CONSTRUCTION AREA.
>>> AND OTHER LOOK FOR ALL YOU
VIRGINIA DRIVERS WHO CAN SOON
HAVE TO WATCH OUT FOR SPEED
CAMERAS WITH A BILL TO ALLOW
THOSE CAMERAS AND VERY SPECIFIC
LOCATIONS IS AWAITING THE
GOVERNOR'S INTERPRET THOSE
PLACEMENTS AND OPERATION OF THE
SPEED CAMERAS COME WITH ALL
KINDS OF CONDITIONS.
>> VIRGINIA DRIVERS HAVE NEVER
HAD TO DEAL WITH SPEED CAMERAS,
AT LEAST NOT IN VIRGINIA.
WE HAVE THEM IN D.C. AND
MARYLAND BUT NOW IT APPEARS
THEY ARE CLOSER THAN EVER.
THEY WILL NOT JUST BE ANYWHERE
BUT IF GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM
SIGNS THE BILL THEY WOULD BE IN
pCONSTRUCTION BOXES LIKE THIS
ONE LEADING UP TO THE MEMORIAL
BRIDGE.
THE RECENT, FATAL ACCIDENTS
HAVE BEEN MORE PREVALENT THAN
EVER BEFORE IN CONSTRUCTION AND
WORK ZONES AND OTHER PEOPLE TO
BRING AND MAKE IT A SAFER
ENVIRONMENT FOR THOSE WORKING
ON OUR ROADS.
HOW WOULD IT WORK?
A POLICE OFFICER WOULD HAVE TO
BE OUT IN A ZONE WITH THEIR
LIGHTS FLASHING.
THEY WOULD HOLD A RADAR GUN OR
SPEED CAMERA GUN IN THEIR HAND
IF YOU ARE GOING MORE THAN 12
MILES PER HOUR OVER THE SPEED
LIMIT, HE WOULD THEN RECEIVE A
$125 FINE IN THE MAIL.
THERE WILL BE WARNING SIGNS
OUT, AT LEAST 1000 FEET BEFORE
THE CONSTRUCTION ZONE TO WARN
THOSE.
AT LEAST THE DRIVERS WHO ARE
PAYING ATTENTION.
AS FOR WHERE THE MONEY WILL GO.
THE $125 FINES WILL ALL GO TO
THE STATE POLICE BUDGET.
STILL NO WORD ON WHEN THE SPEED
CAMERAS COULD HIT THE ROADS IN
VIRGINIA.
REPORTING IN ARLINGTON, I AM
SAM SWEENEY ABC7 NEWS.
>>Adrianna: A LIVE LOOK OUTSIDE
RIGHT NOW AT THE CAPITAL AND
STEVE, IT IS PRETTY WINDY OUT
THERE.
BUT IT IS WARM AND ALSO THE SUN
IS PEEKING THROUGH THE CLOUDS
PARTICIPATE LOOKING AT A NICE
AFTERNOON THROUGHOUT THE DMV.
UR NEW LIFE, FROM THE
WATERGATE HOTEL LOOKING AT THE
POTOMAC, KENNEDY CENTER, THE
PENTAGON AND RIGHT OVER HERE.
LOTS OF SUNSHINE NO MATTER
WHERE YOU ARE THIS AFTERNOON.
LOOK AT THESE TEMPERATURES.
LREADY IN THE LOWER 60S AND
EVEN MIDDLE 60S TO THE WEST OF
D.C.. NOW THE 24 HOUR
TEMPERATURE CHANGE COMPARED TO
YESTERDAY AT THIS TIME, ABOUT
18 DEGREES MODERATE.
WE HAVE A COLD FRONT ON THE WAY
AND LOOK AT THE TEMPERATURE
SHIFT OFF TO THE WEST OF US.
33 DEGREES COLDER THAN JUST 24
HOURS AGO OVER IN CHICAGO.
THE COLD FRONT WILL EVENTUALLY
OVERSPREAD COLD AIR FOR THE
METRO AREA.N THE MEANTIME WE
DO HAVE WINTER WEATHER
ADVISORIES AS WE HEAD OVER TO
KENTUCKY AND SOUTHERN INDIANA
AND INTO ILLINOIS BUT IF YOU
HAVE TRAVEL PLANS TO THE ST.
LOUIS AREA, YOU MIGHT FIND THE
LATEST.
WAS FOR US YOU ARE LOOKING AT A
GOOD LOOKING AFTERNOON WITH A
COLD FRONT ON THE WAY.
EARLY FORECAST FOR YOUR
TEMPERATURES, WE ARE IN THE 60S
WITH ADDED CLOUD COVER FOR THE
AFTERNOON INTO THE EVENING
HOURS.
WE ARE TRACKING THE NEXT
WEATHER MAKER THAT PROMISES TO
BRING A LITTLE BIT OF
ACCUMULATION TO PARTS OF THE
AREA BY EARLY TOMORROW MORNING.
I WILL GIVE YOU THE TIMING WITH
A FRESHLY UPDATED FUTURECAST IN
JUST A FEW MINUTES.
>>Adrianna: IN DEVELOPMENTS NOW
WITH A STORY WE FIRST BROKE ON
SEVEN.
[SCREAMING]
>>Adrianna: THIS IS VIDEO
SHOWING A SCHOOL FIDELITY
STUDENT HERE IN INTENSIVE CARE
WITH A FRACTURED SKULL AND A
BLOOD CLOT.
ABC7 NEWS HAS NOT LEARNED THAT
SCHOOL OFFICIALS DID NOT CALL
9-1-1 BUT THE BOYS PARENTS DID
HOURS LATER.
AS MONTGOMERY COUNTY REPORTER
KEVIN LEWIS FOUND, THAT APPEARS
TO GO AGAINST THE SCHOOL'S OWN
POLICIES.
>> THIS BINDING CONTRACT SIGNED
BY AN CPS AND LOCAL LAW
ENFORCEMENT LEADERS HAS A
SECTION CALLED, INFORMATION
SHARING AND INVESTIGATIONS.T
IS LIST A HANDFUL OF CRITICAL
INCIDENTS, INCLUDING THIS, A
PHYSICAL ATTACK ON ANOTHER THAT
REQUIRES MEDICAL ATTENTION
OUTSIDEOF THE SCHOOL HEALTH
ROOM.
THE DOCUMENT EXPLAINS THE
SCHOOL MUST REPORT ALL CRITICAL
INCIDENTS, QUOTE , AS AS SOON
AS POSSIBLE.
AND BY DIRECT INDICATION WITH
THE SRO OR TO THE PUBLIC SAFETY
COMMUNICATIONS CENTER.
9-1-1. BUT MONTGOMERY COUNTY
POLICE TOLD US THAT NEVER
HAPPENED TUESDAY AFTER THIS
FIGHT AT McGRUDER HIGH SCHOOL
IN DURWOOD WHICH LEFT SHANE VAN
DYCK'S SON IN THE ICU WITH A
FRACTURED SCHOOL AND A BLOOD
CLOT.
>> THEY TOLD HIS MOTHER THAT
YOUR SON IS PEEKING AND WE
THINK YOU NEED TO TAKE HIM TO
THE EMERGENCY ROOM.
>> HE WAS LEFT TO CALL POLICE
AT 2:14 PM.
ABC7 NEWS HAS OBTAINED THE
DISPATCH ALREADY.
>> THE VICTIM WAS ASSAULTED
AROUND THAT TIME AND IS
CURRENTLY IN THE HOSPITAL.
AT CHILDREN'S.
THE FATHER IS ON SCENE.> WE
ASKED AN CPS FOR ON CAMERA
INTERVIEWS WITH SUPERINTENDENT
JACK SMITH AND OR McGRUDER
PRINCIPAL LEROY EVANS PUT BOTH
SAID THEY WERE NOT AVAILABLE.
I AM KEVIN LEWIS, ABC7 NEWS.
>>Adrianna: DURING AMERICAN
HEART MONTH, 7 ON YOUR SIDE IS
SHARING STORIES OF IMPACTS OF
HEART DISEASE.
AMY INTRODUCES US TO AN
ENDURANCE ATHLETE THAT WAS
FOCUSED ON FITNESS AND LEARN
THE WARNING SIGNS OF A DEADLY
HEART ATTACK.
>> MITCH WORKS OUT EVERY DAY.
>> I DO NOT KNOW IF THERE IS
ANYTHING MORE IMPORTANT THAN
TAKING CARE OF YOURSELF.
>> HE WOULD KNOW.
>> ON A SCALE OF 1 TO 10.8.
>> THE SENIOR VICE PRESIDENT OF
FITNESS FOR WHEN MY FITNESS
STARTED MAKING HIS HELD A TOP
PRIORITY AT AGE 15.
>> I DO NOT THINK THERE IS
ANYTHING MORE IMPORTANT.
>> A LITTLE MORE THAN A YEAR
AGO, THE UNTHINKABLE HAPPENED.
>> THEY GAVE ME THE NEWS THAT
YOU HAD A HEART ATTACK IN THE
LAST COUPLE OF DAYS AND IS BAD.
YOU ARE NOT LEAVING HERE.
>> THAT, JUST DAYS AFTER A
THREE HOUR BIKE RIDE AND A RUN
ON THE TREADMILL, WHICH WAS CUT
SHORT FROM THE PAIN.
>> WHO KNOWS WHAT COULD HAVE
HAPPENED.
IT EASILY COULD HAVE GONE IN
ANOTHER DIRECTION.
>> HE ADMITS THAT DURING THE
WORKOUT DAYS PRIOR HE BRUSHED
OFF SOME OF THE WARNING SIGNS.
CHEST PAINS, PAIN IN HIS ARMS
IN HIS JAW WALKING.
>> I SEARCH FOR IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO HAVE A HEART ATTACK SO IT
HAS TO BE SOMETHING ELSE AND
THAT IS WHY I IGNORED IT.
IT COULD NOT BE TRUE.
>> THE ENDURANCE ATHLETE IS
ALWAYS ON THE MOVE, EVEN DURING
A LONG DISTANCE CYCLING TRIP TO
THE MOUNTAINS MONTHS PRIOR, HE
FELT OKAY.
>> THEY BASICALLY SAID, IF YOU
HAVE NOT LIVED THE HEALTHY
LIFESTYLE YOU HAVE LIVED, YOU
CERTAINLY WOULD HAVE DIED.
>> NOW, WHILE HE CANNOT REVERSE
HIS GENETICS, HE IS WATCHING
WHAT HE EATS EVEN MORE CLOSELY.
IN CONTINUING A HEALTHY
LIFESTYLE WITHOUT FEAR.
>>Adrianna: COLORADO MAN SAID
THE LESSONS HE LEARNED FROM THE
CAT OWNER HELPED HIM TO THE
NORTH IN LINE WITH HIS BARE
HANDS.
>> FOR THE FIRST TIME, TRAVIS
IS TELLING HIS STORY ABOUT A
JOG TO THE MOUNTAINS TURNING
INTO A FIGHT FOR HIS LIFE.
>> I ENDED UP HEARING SOME PINE
NEEDLES RUSSELL, LIKE A STICK
BREAK.
I TURNED AROUND AND WAS PRETTY
BUMMED OUT TO SEE A MOUNTAIN
LION CHASING AFTER ME.
I STOPPED AND I THREW MY HANDS
UP IN THE AIR AND I STARTED
SHOUTING AND, IMPORTANTLY, THE
SHELLS DID NOT DETERIORATE.
SO IT JUST KIND OF KEPT RUNNING
AND LUNGED AT ME.
>> THE YOUNG MAN LINE WITH
ABOUT 50 POUNDS AND FOUR FEET
LONG WALKING ONTO HIS HANDS AND
WRIST AND CLAWING AT HIS FACE
AND NECK.
>> THAT IS WITH MY FEAR
RESPONSE TURNED INTO MORE OF A
FIGHT RESPONSE BECAUSE I
REALIZE HOW CLOSE IT WAS
GETTING TO MY EYES BUT.
>> THE 31-YEAR-OLD REFUSING TO
GIVE UP, STRIKING THE ANIMAL
WITH THE STICKS IN A LARGE
ROCK.
>> FORTUNATELY, I HAD A TOUGH
TIME SWINGING IT WITH MY ARM
WALKED IN THE CAT'S JAWS.
>> FINALLY GETTING THE UPPER
HAND.
>> A COUPLE OF MINUTES LATER IT
FINALLY STOPPED MOVING.
THEN THE JAWS OPENED AND I WAS
ABLE TO SCRIBBLE BACK UP THE
HILL AND GET THE HECK OUT OF
DODGE.
>> HE ENDED UP WITH NEARLY 30
STITCHES AND A REPUTATION
RIVALING CHUCK NORRIS.
>> CHUCK WOULD HAVE COME OUT
WITHOUT A SCRATCH.
YOU KNOW HIM.
>> WILDLIFE EXPERTS SAY HE DID
EVERYTHING RIGHT WHEN THE CAT
APPEARED.
THE ADVISEMENT DO NOT RUN.
RAISE YOUR ARMS TO LOOK BIGGER
AND FACE THE CAT AND TALK
FIRMLY.
IF IT ATTACKS THE FIGHT.
>>Adrianna: THAT WAS CLEAN SEND
OUT REPORTING THAT A CALIFORNIA
BOY WHO HAS A RARE MEDICAL
CONDITION IS THROAT AFTER
LIVING OUT HIS DREAM.
TAKE A LOOK HERE.
LEMUEL MILLER GREENFIELD HAS
ALWAYS WANTED TO BE A POLICE
OFFICER.
THE SACRAMENTO POLICE
DEPARTMENT GAVE HIM A SHOT.
HE GOT TO SPEND THE DAY AS AN
OFFICER AND HIS CLASSMATES SENT
HIM OFF IN STYLE.
>> HE ALWAYS HAS A POSITIVE
ATTITUD.
EVEN WHEN THINGS ARE ROUGH.
>> HE SEEMED TO LOVE IT.
WE WERE ALL TAKING PICTURES AND
HE WAS EXCITED.
>> AS WE ARE DRIVING HE IS
LEARNING HOW TO USE THE SIREN
IN PA SYSTEM.
WE ARE JUST HAPPY THAT WE CAN
MAKE HIS DAY.
>>Adrianna: ONCE MILLER ARRIVED
AT THE POLICE ACADEMY HE TOOK
PART IN TARGET PRACTICE AND HE
EVEN HANDCUFFED A SUSPECT WHO
WAS WANTED FOR STEALING DONUTS.
MAKE WHATEVER YOU ARE SNIFFING
AND OTHER DID FOR YOU FOR
VALENTINE'S DAY, IT WAS
PROBABLY NOT AS EXTREME AS WHAT
WE ARE ABOUT TO SHOW YOU.
CONNIE WEST SUPPRESSING HIS
WIFE WITH A ROOM FULL OF ROSES
AND KENNY G. THE SAXOPHONIST
WAS THERE TO SENATE COMPRESSION
WEST AND SHE POSTED THIS VIDEO
AND A PICTURE TO HER TWITTER
PAGE YESTERDAY SAYING, BEST
HUSBAND AWARD GOES TO MINE.
MOST THOUGHTFUL GIFTS EVER.
>>> A CLASSIC VIDEO GAMES
SETTING A NEW WORLD RECORD
PRICE WITH A MINT CONDITION
COPY OF THE ORIGINAL SUPER
MARIO BROTHERS HAS SOLD FOR
JUST OVER $100,000 AT AUCTION.
THE GAME WAS RELEASED BY
NINTENDO BACK IN 1985 AND THIS
COPYRIGHT HERE, HAS NEVER BEEN
OPENED.
>>Steve: PERIOD.
I HAD THAT GAME.
>>Adrianna: HOW MUCH CAN YOU
SELL IT FOR TODAY?
>>Steve: I DO NOT KNOW WHERE IT
IS.
>>Adrianna: IT IS WORTH
NOTHING.
>>Steve: I STOP ALL MY LEGOS.
THEY ARE WORTH A LOT.
WHEN ARE THEY VINTAGE LEGOS?
>>Steve: THEY ARE ORIGINALS.
HE GOOD STUFF.
I HAVE A WHOLE CITY.
>>> HERE IS OUR?
TOP THE WATERGATE HOTEL IN HERE
IS THE VIEW.
LOOKING TOWARD ROSLYN, THE
EVER-CHANGING SKYLINE, CITY
CENTER AND YOU CAN SEE, IS IT
CITY CENTER OR CENTER CITY?
>>Adrianna: CITY CENTER?
>>Steve: A LOT OF STORES AND
STUFF GOING ON THERE.
>>Adrianna: AND BARS.
>>Steve: EXACTLY.
OVER TOWARD OUR BUILDINGS HERE
AT ABC 7. LOOKING AT A FEW
PASSING CLOUDS BUT OTHERWISE A
NICE AMOUNT AFTERNOON SHAPING
UP FOR NOT ONLY THE DMV BUT FOR
THE MID ATLANTIC.
REAGAN NATIONAL AIRPORT AND A
LOT OF FOLKS ARE GETTING OUT
EARLY FOR THE LONG HOLIDAY
WEEKEND AND LOOKING GOOD FOR
YOUR TRAVEL PLANS.
AT LEAST FOR OF THE WEST COAST
BUT WE MIGHT RUN INTO PROBLEMS
IN THE MID PART OF THE COUNTRY
WITH WINTRY WEATHER.
HE BELIEVED WE ARE ALREADY
TALKING ABOUT OUR PAUL REPORT?
TREE POLLEN, IF YOU HAVE BEEN
SNIFFLING AND SNEEZING, AND ON
THE HIGH CATEGORY.
GRASPING NOT TO WORRY ABOUT,
PLEASE DELAY NOT AND MOLD IS IN
THE LOW CATEGORY WITH 60
DEGREES OF RECOGNITION, 59
WINCHESTER, 43 IN CUMBERLAND.
TO HAVE WINDS UPWARD OF 15 TO
20 MILES PER HOUR BUT A
TEMPERATURE CHANGE COMPARED TO
YESTERDAY AT THIS EXACT TIME
ABOUT 20 DEGREES WARMER.
I WILL NOT ARGUE WITH THAT.
FEBRUARY.
STORM WATCH 7 SATELLITE AND
RADAR WITHOUT A CLOUD COVER
MOVING IN FOR THE AFTERNOON
HOURS.
I SEE A FEW SPINDLES ALONG THE
MASON-DIXON LINE AND I DO NOT
ANTICIPATE THAT WILL AMOUNT TO
A LOT.
GOING OUT TO LUNCH ON THE SPOT?
LOOKING AT 60S AND GRABBED THE
SUNGLASSES AND A LIGHT JACKET
AND THAT IS ALL YOU NEED ADDED
CLOUD COVER FOR THIS EVENING
AND TEMPERATURES FALL TO THE
50S AND BY TONIGHT WE ARE
DROPPING INTO THE UPPER 20S TO
LOWER TO MIDDLE 30S AROUND 35
TO 38 DEGREES INSIDE THE
BELTWAY.
WITH THE COLDEST AIR ALONG THE
I-81 CORRIDOR.
TOMORROW, YOU HAVE HEARD A LOT
ABOUT THE POTENTIAL FOR A
LITTLE BIT OF WINTRY WEATHER.
WE WILL SEE MORE CLOUDS AND SUN
DURING THE FIRST HALF OF THE
DAY BUT THEN OUR SKIES WILL
BEGIN TO CLEAR.
AS THE SYSTEM MOVES OUT OF
HERE.
HERE IS OUR FUTURECAST THAT
WILL TAKE US TO THIS AFTERNOON,
THROUGH THE AFTERNOON HOURS AND
CALL DISCUSS ACROSS THE AREA.
WE ARE STILL DRY BUT THEN COME
EARLY TOMORROW MORNING WE ARE
WATCHING HIS SYSTEM THAT WILL
APPROACH FROM THE WEST BUT IT
IS A FRESHLY UPDATED FUTURECAST
WITHIN THE LAST 10 MINUTES BUT
NOTICE HOW IT KEEPS EVERYTHING
WILL GO TO THE SOUTH OF THE
.C. METRO AREA.SOUTH OF THE
THE SYSTEM KEEPS MOVING FURTHER
AND FURTHER SOUTH WHICH MEANS
LESS OF AN IMPACT ON THE METRO
IN TERMS OF ANY ACCUMULATION.
IF WE DO SEE ANY CUMULATING
SNOW IT WILL BE WET AND SLUSHY.
IT WILL NOT AMOUNT TO A WHOLE
LOT, MAINLY ON THE GRASSY
AREAS.
FOR THE DISTRICT, ARLINGTON AND
ALEXANDRIA, I DO NOT EXPECT
HARDLY ANYTHING AT ALL.
BUT THEN GO TO SOUTHERN
MARYLAND AND OVER TOWARD THE
CITY AND FOR EXPORT AND MAYBE
AN INCH AT BEST.
IF EVEN THAT.
HE MIGHT HAVE TO LOWER IT EVEN
MORE BUT HERE IS OUR FORECAST
FOR THE NEXT SEVEN DAYS WITH
THE WINTRY MIX FOR TOMORROW AND
THE SAME AS WE HEAD INTO THE
DAY ON SUNDAY.
AS WE MOVE INTO PRESIDENT'S DAY
IT IS DRY WITH TEMPERATURES IN
THE UPPER 40S.
OUR NEXT BIG WEATHER MAKER FOR
THIS WEEKEND APPEARS TO BE THE
MIDDLE OF THE UPCOMING WEEK.
LOOKING AT TEMPERATURES THAT
WILL GO FROM THE MID-30S TO THE
50 DEGREES RANGE.
WE COULD BE LOOKING AT WINTRY
WEATHER BY WEDNESDAY.
THE EVER-CHANGING FORECAST FOR
THE WEEKEND, COMPARED TO WHAT
WE THOUGHT A FEW DAYS AGO, IS
SHAPING UP TO BE A LOT BETTER
THAN ANTICIPATED.
>>Adrianna: WE WILL TAKE IT.
THANK YOU STEVE.
>>> FACEBOOK TURNED 15 THIS
WEEK BUT MANY ARE NOT
CELEBRATING.
SPECIAL THOSE WHO FELL VICTIM
TO ONE OF THE MOST SUCCESSFUL
SCAMS SO FAR THIS YEAR.
CONSUMER REPORTER JOHN MURRAY
SHOWS US WHAT IT IS SO EASY TO
FALL FOR THIS SO YOU DO NOT
WASTE YOUR MONEY.
>> PEOPLE ALL OVER THE D.C.
AREA AND ELSEWHERE ARE FALLING
FOR THE FACEBOOK GRANT SCAM.
WITH THIS AND MONEY TRYING TO
GET A NONEXISTENT GOVERNMENT
GRANT.
WHAT IS THE SCAMS SO
SUCCESSFUL?
BECAUSE IT INVOLVES ONE OF YOUR
BEST FRIENDS AS ONE VICTIM
FOUND OUT.
>> BEVERLY AND JENNIFER HAVE
BEEN FRIENDS FOREVER.
SO WHEN BEV SENT JENNIFER A
FACEBOOK MESSAGE SAYING SHE
JUST RECEIVED A BIG GOVERNMENT
GRANT.
>> HOW MUCH MONEY DID SHE SAY
SHE GOT?
>> $50,000.
>> JENNIFER WANT TO KNOW IF SHE
COULD APPLY TO.
>> SHE SAID TO CHECK INTO IT
BECAUSE THERE IS A POSSIBILITY
THAT I COULD GET IT.
>> JENNIFER, COPING WITH HEALTH
AND MONEY PROBLEMS CONTACT THE
GRANT AGENT AND SHE LEARNED
THAT SHE TO QUALIFIED FOR MONEY
IF SHE JUST PAID AN UPFRONT FEE
OF --
>> $700.
>> TRUSTING HER FRIEND SHE
DECIDED TO SEND IT IN IN DOING
SO SHE BECAME THE LATEST VICTIM
OF THE FACEBOOK GRANT SCAM.
SIMILAR CASES THE SCAM VICTIM
SINCE GIFT CARDS AND THE MONEY
IS LOST FOREVER.
BUT IN THIS CASE JENNIFER WENT
TO HER BANK AND SENT THE MONEY
THROUGH WESTERN UNION SO AT
LEAST THERE WAS A PAPER TRAIL.
>> ARE READ INTO HER FRIDAY
NIGHT.
>> SHE ASKED ABOUT THE
MESSAGES.> YOU WERE TELLING
ME THAT HE GOT A $50,000 GRANT.
FROM A CERTAIN PLACE.
AND SHE SAID, THAT WAS NOT ME.
AND I SIT HERE IS A PICTURE OF
YOU.
>> YOU DO NOT SEND ANY THOSE
MESSAGES,
>> NONE OF THEM.
NO.
NONE OF THEM.
NOT A ONE.
>> OUR FACEBOOK PAGE HAD BEEN
I wanted more from
my COPD medicine...
...that's why I've got the Power
of 1-2-3 medicines with TRELEGY.
The only FDA-approved
3-in-1 COPD treatment.
♪ TRELEGY. The Power of 1-2-3 ♪
♪ TRELEGY 1-2-3 TRELEGY ♪
With TRELEGY and the Power of
1-2-3, I'm breathing better.
TRELEGY works 3 ways to...
...open airways,...
...keep them open...
...and reduce inflammation...
...for 24 hours
of better breathing.
TRELEGY won't replace
a rescue inhaler
for sudden breathing problems.
TRELEGY is NOT for asthma.
Tell your doctor if you
have a heart condition
or high blood pressure
before taking it.
Do not take TRELEGY
more than prescribed.
TRELEGY may increase your
risk of thrush, pneumonia,
and osteoporosis.
Call your doctor if worsened
breathing, chest pain,
mouth or tongue swelling,..
...problems urinating, vision
changes, or eye pain occur.
Think your COPD
medicine is doing enough?
Maybe you should think again.
Ask your doctor about once-daily
TRELEGY and the
Power of 1-2-3.
♪ TRELEGY 1-2-3 ♪
Save at TRELEGY.com.
>>Adrianna: THE MUELLER PROBE
HAS STACKED OF INDICTMENTS AND
CONVICTIONS IN TRUMP SKIPPING
AND INNER-CIRCLE.
IS THERE ANOTHER ANGLE TO THE
STORE YOU HAVE NOT HEARD ABOUT?
FULL MEASURE CHERYL ATKINSON
JOINS US NOW AND IS GOOD TO
TALK TO YOU.
THIS DEALS WITH SOME IN OUR
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY.
TELL US ABOUT IT.
>> WE HAVE SPENT A LOT OF
ATTENTION ON THE MUELLER PROBE
AND SO FAR NO PUBLIC EVIDENCE
OF INVOLVEMENT BETWEEN
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND RUSSIAN
PRESIDENT PUTIN AS WAS ALLEGED.
THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF EVIDENCE
OVER THE PAST TWO YEARS THAT
HAS COME OUT ABOUT ALLEGED
SURVEILLANCE ABUSES COMMITTED
BY SOME INSIDE OUR INTELLIGENCE
COMMUNITY.
NOT JUST 2016 BUT IN THE DECADE
AND AND A HALF+ BEFORE THAT.
WE WILL GO OVER THE EVIDENCE
AND LOOK AT THE PART OF THE
STORE IN OUR COVER STORY THIS
WEEK.
>>Adrianna: LOOKING FORWARD TO
IT.
ALSO THIS WEEK, A TRIP TO A
WHIMSICAL TIKI BAR IN MONTANA.
WHAT MAKES THIS SO UNIQUE?
>> WHILE WE WERE IN MONTANA
SHOOTING IS FOR ON THEIR
HEALTHCARE SOLUTIONS, WE FOUND
A LITTLE TIKI BAR IN THE MIDDLE
OF SNOW IN MONTANA FOR THE
PATIENTS COME, BRING THEIR
FAMILIES AND SO ON.HEY HAVE
FOOD AND DRINK AND WATCH
MERMAIDS SWIMMING AROUND IN A
TANK UNDERGROUND THAT THEY CAN
SEE IN THE BAR.
WE CAN TALK YOU SEE WHAT
HAPPENS WHEN THE MERMAN, THE
MALE MERMAID GETS IN THE WATER
WITH HIS GIRLFRIEND AND HE WILL
HAVE FUN SEEING, IT IS A FAMILY
SHOW AND IS SOMETHING THE WHOLE
FAMILY CAN WATCH.
>>Adrianna: LOOKING FORWARD TO
IT.
THAN
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>Adrianna: MUST SEE VIDEO
RIGHT NOW.
YOU'VE SEEN HUGE VEGETABLES
BEFORE, BUT WHAT ABOUT THIS
HUMAN SIZED CABBAGE?
THIS AUSTRALIAN COUPLE GREW
THIS VEGGIE INTENSE MEDIA.
THEY MANAGED TO KEEP OUT THE
WALLABIES, POSSUMS, SLUGS AND
BUTTERFLIES WITH WIRE FENCING
AND A FINE NET.
THAT MASSIVE CABBAGE PRODUCED
TWO WEEKS OF COASTAL, SALADS
AND A TRADITIONAL GERMAN
CABBAGE DISH.
>>Steve: ONLY TWO WEEKS?
>>Adrianna: AND NO.
>>Steve: MY GOODNESS.
CRAZY STUFF IN TASMANIA.
>>> OUR WEATHER FORECAST
LOOKING REALLY FANTASTIC.
SHOULD'VE OF THE TEMPERATURE TO
65 AND MAYBE 66 DEGREES BECAUSE
PARTS OF THE AREA WILL SEE
TEMPERATURES THAT FORM BUT A
COLD FRONT LATER TODAY WILL
DROP OUR TIMBERS OVERNIGHT IN A
CHILLY DAY TOMORROW.
ESPECIALLY COMPARED TO THE
TODAY WITH A BETTER CHANCE OF
WINTRY MIX AS YOU MOVE INTO
TOMORROW MORNING.
MINUTES OUT OF TOWN.
REALLY SOUTH OF THE D.C. AREA.
THIS POINT IT DOES NOT LOOK
LIKE IT WILL BE A WHOLE LOT FOR
ARTS.
A FEW CHANCE FOR SHOWERS MAYBE
A FEW SNOWFLAKES MOVING INTO
SUNDAY.RESIDENT'S DAY IS DRY
WITH UPPER 40S AND COOLER ON
TUESDAY.
THAT IS GOING TO SET THE STAGE
FOR POTENTIALLY WINTRY WEATHER
ALONG THE METRO AREA BY
WEDNESDAY OF NEXT WEEK WITH
TEMPERATURES IN THE 30S.
THE EVER-CHANGING FORECAST, WE
WILL KEEP YOU UPDATED ON WJLA
24/7 THIS AFTERNOON AND BILL
KELLY WILL BE IN AT 4:00 AND WE
WILL GIVE YOU A FRESH LOOK AT
THE FORECAST.
OUR FUTURECAST IS ALWAYS
UPDATING AND THE LATEST WHEN
THEY CAME IN HOUSES SYSTEM EVEN
FURT