>> NOW ABC7 NEWS AT NOON.
ON YOUR SIDE.
>>Lindsey: WE ARE WISHING YOU A
HAPPY FOURTH OF JULY AS A COME
ON AIR AT NOON.
RAINS ACROSS THE NATION ARE
CELEBRATING AMERICA.
MANY EVENTS ARE HAPPENING IN
OUR AREA AND THEIR HAPPENING
RIGHT NOW.
THE NATIONAL INDEPENDENCE DAY
PARADE IS JUST KICKING OFF.
THE HAPPENED A SHORT TIME AGO.
FOR NOW IT LOOKS LIKE THE
WEATHER IS COOPERATING, BUT WE
ARE BRACING FOR SOME STORMS AND
SEAFOOD AND HAS THE TIMING AND
HE IS TRACKING ALL OF THIS FOR
US.
STEVE, HAPPY FOURTH TO YOU.
>>Steve: SEEM TO YOU LINDSAY.
LOOK AT THE GREATEST THREAT FOR
THE STRONGER STORMS AND HEAVY
DOWNPOURS LATER THIS AFTERNOON
INTO THE EARLY EVENING HOURS.
LOOK DOWNSTREAM FROM THE
POTOMAC FROM OUR, TOP THE
WATERGATE HOTEL WHICH WE ARE
DRY RIGHT NOW BUT THAT WILL
CHANGE FOR THE NEXT SEVERAL
HOURS BUT WE DO HAVE A FLASH
FLOOD WATCH FOR THE D.C. METRO
INCLUDING MONTGOMERY COUNTY,
FAIRFAX, ARLINGTON, ALEXANDRIA,
THE DISTRICT AND PRINCE
GEORGE'S.
ALSO PARTS OF LOUDOUN COUNTY
UNTIL 8:00 P.M. TONIGHT.
HERE IS STORMWATCH 7 SATELLITE
AND RADAR WITH A FEW SHOWERS
BEGIN TO BUBBLE UP.
JUST ACROSS NORTHEAST D.C. OVER
TOWARD PARKLAND AND MOVING OUT
TOWARD THE NORTH AND EAST.
NOTHING HEAVY RIGHT NOW BUT AS
MENTIONED, THAT WILL CHANGE AS
WE HEAD TO THE NEXT SEVERAL
HOURS.
HERE IS OUR FUTURECAST HERE IS
THE HIGH-RESOLUTION MODEL AND
WILL STOP AT 2:00.
LOOK AT HOW QUICKLY THE MODEL
HAS THOSE STORMS POPPING UP.
THEY DO NOT MOVE VERY FAST AND
THEY COULD BRING HEAVY RAIN TO
THE DISTRICT IN ARLINGTON AND
ALEXANDRIA AT 4:00 P.M. AND
CONTINUE AS WE MOVE INTO THE
ALL IMPORTANT 6:00 AND 7:00
HOUR.
IF THERE IS ANY GOOD NEWS.
BY 8:00 TONIGHT SHOWERS BECOME
MORE LIMITED AND THE FIREWORKS
DISPLAY SET TO BEGIN AT 7:00
P.M. IT SHOULD GON.
AT LEAST, ACCORDING TO THIS
MODEL HERE.LTHOUGH THE CLOUD
DECK MAYBE A LITTLE ON THE LOW
SIDE WORTH WATCHING AND WE WILL
KEEP YOU UPDATED LOOK AT THESE
TEMPERATURES0 DEGREES
ALREADY AT REAGAN NATIONAL
AIRPORT THAT IS JUST PART OF
THE STORY WITH FEELS LIKE IN
THE MIDDLE 90S BUT WE HAVE A
HEAT EMERGENCY POSTER FOR THE
DISTRICT AND THAT IS DONE BY
THE DISTRICT GOVERNMENT.
COOLING CENTERS ARE OPEN FOR
THOSE WHO NEED THEM.
COMING UP IN A FEW MINUTES, AND
UPDATED LOOK AT OUR FUTURECAST
POSSIBILITY HEAD THROUGH THE
REST OF THE LONG HOLIDAY
WEEKEND.
>>Lindsey: ALL RIGHT STEVE.
WE DO WANT TO TALK ABOUT THAT.
THE WEATHER IS HOLDING UP SO
FAR FOR THE NATIONAL
INDEPENDENCE DAY PARADE AND
NATHAN BUCKET IS THERE.
NATHAN, HAPPY FOURTH OF JULY TO
YOU.
JUST HOW CROWDED IS IT RIGHT
NOW?
>>Reporter: IT IS GETTING MORE
CROWDED AND I WILL SHOW YOU THE
SITUATION.
I AM GOING DO SOME CROWD
SURFING.
EYE ON SEVENTH APPROACHING
CONSTITUTION AVENUE AND THEY
ARE TELLING EVERYBODY TO MOVE
BACK FROM THE STREET.
PEOPLE WANT TO CROWD ONTO THE
STREET AND I AM HAVING TO MOVE
AROUND.
>>> HAPPY FOURTH OF JULY
pEVERYONE.
>>> THIS IS WHAT IS GOING ON TO
GIVE THE CONTEXT WITH HIS
NATIONAL ARCHIVES OVER HERE AND
YOU SEE SOME PEOPLE HERE
CELEBRATING THE FOURTH OF JULY.
WERE YOU VISITING FROM?
ANYBODY?
>> ATLANTA!
>> TENNESSEE!
>> WASHINGTON D.C.!
>> YOU ARE LOCAL.
GOOD.
THE CONTEXT POLICE ARE TELLING
PEOPLE TO STAY BACK THERE THERE
IS THE PARADE AND I WILL SHOW
YOU SOME OF THE FLOATS DOWN THE
WAY.
WE HAVE NOTICED SOME BANDS AND
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN COMING TO HEAR
THE FANS BUT IN FACT, THIS IS
WHAT SOME PEOPLE WHO WERE
VISITING FROM ALEXANDRIA FOR
THE FIRST TIME BUT ALSO FROM
GEORGIA HAD TO SAY.
>> THE REASON WE ARE OUT HERE
TO CELEBRATE THE INDEPENDENCE
FROM GREAT BRITAIN.LSO, OUR
NATION OVER THE LAST 243 YEARS
REALLY.
AND TO BE A MONK'S PAGES.
>> I SEE EVERYBODY COMING
TOGETHER AND IT MAKES ME HAPPY
BUT WE ARE NOT SEEING ANYTHING
VULGAR LIKE ANYTHING UGLY IT
MAKES ME HAPPY EVERY IS HERE
TOGETHER TO CELEBRATE AND IT
SEEMS LIKE A GREAT DAY.
>>Reporter: TALKING ABOUT ONE
OF THOSE BANDS PRETTY EASY ONE
OF THOSE BANDS AND THAT IS WHAT
SHE WAS COMING TO HEAR.HERE
ARE PLENTY MORE BANDS AND
FLOATS COMING UP.
AGAIN, THE SITUATION IS THAT WE
HAVE A LOT MORE, I WOULD SAY A
LOT MORE POLITICAL SCIENCE AND
A LOT MORE POLITICAL HATS AND
ADVERTISEMENTS THAT TYPICALLY
WOULD SEE AT A FOURTH OF JULY
PARADE.
A LOT OF FOLKS ARE HERE COMING
IN FROM ALL AROUND THE COUNTRY
AND HOPING TO GET A GOOD PARTY
IN A GOOD OLD D.C. PARADE.
REPORTING LIVE FROM
CONSTITUTION AND SEVENTH NATHAN
BUCKET ABC7 NEWS.
>>Lindsey: NATHAN, ENJOY IT
DOWN THERE AND THAT IS JUST ONE
OF MANY PARADES GOING ON IN OUR
AREA.
THE STREETS OF ARLINGTON.
IT WAS PACKED THERE FOR THE
ANNUAL PARADE.
THIS EVENING PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
GOING TO GIVE HIS SALUTE TO
AMERICA WITH INDEPENDENCE
EXTRAVAGANZA FEATURING TANKS,
MILITARY FLYOVERS AND A SPEECH
AT THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL.
SOME SAY THE PRESIDENT IS
POLITICIZING A NATIONAL HOLIDAY
BUT WE HAVE THE VERY LATEST.
>>Reporter: IT WILL BE THE SHOW
OF A LIFETIME, PRESIDENT TRUMP
HAS PROMISED ON TWITTER AHEAD
OF HRAVAGANT FOURTH OF
JULY CELEBRATION.
A COSTLY PRODUCTION THAT TRUMP
HAS ALSO PROMISED WILL BE WORTH
THE EXPENSE WITH AN ARRAY OF
MILITARY HARDWARE ON DISPLAY
THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL, INCLUDING
TANKS THAT HAVE ALREADY BEEN
USHERED IN THE SALUTE TO
AMERICA SPECTACLE WILL ALSO
INCLUDE MULTIPLE MILITARY
FLYOVERS AND AN EXTENDED
FIREWORKS SHOW TOPPED OFF WITH
A SPEECH FROM THE COMMANDER IN
CHIEF HIMSELF.
>> WE WILL HAVE PLANES GONG
OVERHEAD, THE BEST FIGHTER JETS
IN THE WORLD AND OTHER PLANES,
>> THE EVENT IS SETTING OF MORE
THAN PYROTECHNIC DEVICES BUT IT
IS ALSO SPARKING BACKLASH FROM
CRITICS WHO ACCUSE THE
PRESIDENT OF STAGING GLORIFIED
CAMPAIGN RALLY AND TURNING THE
CELEBRATION INTO A PARTISAN
EVENT.
THE EVENT IS FREE BUT THE WHITE
HOUSE HAS GIVEN VIP TICKETS TO
THE REPUBLICAN NATIONAL
COMMITTEE AND TOP DONORS BUT
CARSON AND 2020 DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES SETH
MOULTON CALLING THE TRUMP
CELEBRATION, UN-AMERICAN.
>> IT REMINDS ME OF THE SOVIET
UNION.
IT IS UNPATRIOTIC BECAUSE,
MILITARISM IS NOT WHAT AMERICAN
PATRIOTISM IS ABOUT.
>>Reporter: AS FOR THE PRICE
TAG BUT RATHER THE MINISTRATION
NOR THE PENTAGON HAS SCHOOLS
WITH THE COST WILL BE TO
TAXPAYERS.
WE HAVE LEARNED THE NATIONAL
PARK SERVICE IS DIVERTING $2.5
PROJECTS BUT PRESIDENT TRUMP
ADDING OVERNIGHT, THE FIREWORKS
HAVE BEEN DONATED AND THE COST
WILL BE VERY LITTLE COMPARED TO
WHAT IT IS WORTH.
>>Lindsey: THE $750,000 OF
TARIFFS WERE DONATED BY AN OHIO
COMPANY THAT LOBBIED THE
PRESIDENT LAST MONTH TO HOLD
OFF ON THE TARIFFS FOR CHINA.
THE PRESIDENT KNOWS HE WOULD DO
SO THE SAME DAY HE ANNOUNCED
THE DONATION.
ABC NEWS WASHINGTON.
>>Lindsey: SECURITY WILL BE
TIED DOWNTOWN TODAY AND TONIGHT
FOR INDEPENDENCE DAY
CELEBRATIONS AND FOR PRESIDENT
TRUMP SALUTE TO AMERICA.
EACH EVENT HASSTRICT GUIDELINES
ON WHAT YOU CAN BRING AND WHAT
YOU CANNOT THE PRIORITY IS
SAFETY.
NO WEAPONS, NO ALCOHOL, NOT
EVEN DRONES OR BALLOONS ARE
ALLOWED .
FOR THE SALUTE TO AMERICA, NO
BACKPACKS, NO LARGE PURCHASE,
COOLERS OR TABLETS.
FOR COMPLETE LIST YOU CAN HEAD
TO OUR WEBSITE WJLA.com.
YOU CAN FIND EVERYTHING THAT
YOU NEEDED TO KNOW FOR TODAY
ALL IN ONE LIST WHETHER YOU
WERE HEADING TO EVENTS, WANTING
TO AVOID THE CITY ARE WATCHING
FIREWORKS IN YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD.
IT IS ALL ON OUR FREE ABC7 NEWS
APP.
>>> WITH A REMINDER THIS
INDEPENDENT SAY THAT FIREWORKS
ARE NOT TOYS BUT THEY NEED TO
BE USED PROPERLY.
CONSUMER PRODUCT SAFETY
COMMISSION ALWAYS DO THESE
LIMITATIONS ON THE NATIONAL
MALL THIS IS WHAT THEY DID LAST
WEEK WITH COLETTE LIKE TO DO
THESE DEMONSTRATIONS TO SHOW
HOW QUICKLY THINGS CAN GO WRONG
WHEN FIREWORKS ARE NOT HANDLED
PROPERLY.
NEW DATA REVEALS THAT EMERGENCY
ROOMS ACROSS THE U.S.TREATED
MORE THAN 9000 FIREWORKS
RELATED INJURIES LAST YEAR.
MORE THAN HALF OF THOSE
INTERESTS INVOLVED YOUNG
CHEN , VOLVING YOUNG
CHILDREN THAT WERE CAUSED BY
SPARKLERS.
>>> HAPPENING RIGHT NOW.
THE 103RD ANNUAL NATHAN HOT DOG
EATING CONTEST IS GOING ON IN
CONEY ISLAND NEW YORK WITH
LONGTIME CHAMP JOEY CHESTNUT
LOOKS HE MIGHT MAKE HISTORY
AGAIN.
HE SET A WORLD RECORD LAST YEAR
AND HE ATE SALMON FOR HOT DOGS
IN 10 MINUTES.
WE ARE MONITORING THAT IN OF
COURSE, WE WILL HAVE SOME VIDEO
FOR YOU LATER.
COMING UP NEXT AT NOON.
IT IS PROBABLY THE LARGE
DISPLAY OF STARS AND STRIPES
YOU SEE THIS HOLIDAY WITH FIND
OUT WHERE THIS IS.
PLUS.
>>Lindsey: THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT IS HITTING RIVERS ON
HIS COURSE OF THIS CENSUS
ASSISTANTSHIP QUESTION.
THEY TREATED THAT THE FORM OF
COMMERCE ANTIOQUIA WORKING HARD
ON THIS HOLIDAY TO KEEP THAT
QUESTION.S TREVOR AULT
REPORTS, A JUDGE'S ORDER
DEMONSTRATION TO RESOLVE THE
CONFLICT BY TOMORROW.
>> WEEK REMOVED, SUPREME COURT
DECISION BLOCKING DEMONSTRATION
FROM ADDING A CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION TO THE 2020 CENSUS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS NOTIFIED,
JOINING THE DEPARTMENT OF
COMMERCE AND DEPARTMENT OF
JUSTICE ARE WORKING VERY HARD
ON THIS EVEN ON THE FOURTH OF
JULY.
THAT MESSAGE CONTRADICTING THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT'S
ANNOUNCEMENT THAT CENSUS FORMS
ARE BEING PRINTED WITHOUT THE
QUESTION, ARE YOU A U.S.
CITIZEN.
>> I THINK IT IS VERY IMPORTANT
TO FIND OUT IF SOMEBODY IS A
CITIZEN AS OPPOSED TO AN
ILLEGAL.
>> WHAT A PERSON IS INSISTENT
THAT THE FIGHT FOR THE
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION IS
ONGOING, HIS COMMENTS HAVE
SPARKED CONFUSION.
MARYLAND FEDERAL JUDGE CONVENED
A CONFERENCE CALL ON WAS AFTER
SHE SAW THE PRESENCE TO SAYING
THAT REPORTS THAT THE QUESTION
HAD BEEN DROPPED OR FAKE.
ON THE CALL THEY CANNOT EXPLAIN
THE PRESIDENT'S RHETORIC BUT
WHENWE ARE SICK, THE TWEET THIS
ONE WAS THE FIRST I HAD HEARD
OF THE PRESIDENT'S POSITION ON
THIS ISSUE.
I DO NOT HAVE A DEEPER
UNDERSTANDING WHAT THAT MEANS
AT THIS JUNCTURE OTHER THAN
WHAT THE PRESIDENT HAS TWEETED.
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT DID
ADMIT THAT THE PRESIDENT
CONTRADICTED THEM , BUT SAID
THEY HAVE BEEN STARTED TO
EXPLORE WHETHER THERE IS A PATH
FOR CONSISTENT WITH THE SUPREME
COURT TO ALLOW THE CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAD
PREVIOUSLY ARGUED THEY NEEDED
THE CENSUS QUESTION TO BETTER
ENFORCE THE VOTING RIGHTS ACT.
CHIEF JUSTICE JOHN ROBERTS SHOT
DOWN THAT LINE OF THINKING:
CONTROL AND WOULD.
>> THE COURT RULED THAT THE
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION WAS NOT
ABOUT WHATEVER COCKAMAMIE
REASON THAT DONALD TRUMP GAVE
FOR IT.
>> WHILE THE DEPARTMENT OF
JUSTICE IS FOLLOWING THE
PRESENCE INSTRUCTIONS THEY ARE
RUNNING LOW ON TIME.
THE ONLY HAVE UNTIL TOMORROW TO
EXPAND TO THE COURTS HOW THEY
PLAN TO COMPLY WITH THE SUPREME
COURT'S RULING.
TREVOR AULT ABC NEWS
WASHINGTON.
>>Lindsey: WE HAVE AN UPDATE
FOLLOWING MONDAY'S VIOLENT
PROTEST IN HONG KONG WITH
HUNDREDS OF PROTESTERS WREAKED
HAVOC INSIDE THE CITY'S
LEGISLATIVE BUILDING.
FOUR OF THEM ARE NOW TALKING
ABOUT WHY THEY DID IT.
THEY TOLD THE ASSOCIATED PRESS
THAT THE REFUSAL OF CITY
LEADERS TO LISTEN TO THEIR
DEMANDS DRE THEM TO
DESPERATION.
THEY SAY THAT THEY CONCLUDED,
PEACEFUL DEMONSTRATIONS WERE
POINTLESS AFTER THE FAILURE OF
HONG KONG'S PRO-DEMOCRACY AND
BULLET MOVEMENT IN 2014.
>>> PRETTY SURE A LOT OF YOU
MIGHT HAVE BEEN FREAKING OUT A
LITTLE BIT AFTER REALIZING YOUR
INSTAGRAM, FACEBOOK, WHAT'S UP
ACCOUNTS WERE NOT WORKING THE
WAY THEY WERE SUPPOSED TO
YESTERDAY.
THOSE ISSUES HAVE BEEN
RESOLVED.
USERS ON SOCIAL MEDIA PLATFORMS
SAY THEY WERE HAVING TROUBLE
UPLOADING OR SENDING IMAGES AND
THERE IS NO WORD YET ON WHAT
MIGHVE CAUSED THAT ISSUE.
>>> TEAM USA NOW KNOWS WHO THEY
WILL BE FACING IN THE WORLD CUP
FINAL ON SUNDAY.
IT WILL BE THE NETHERLANDS.
THEY WERE ABLE TO KNOCK OUT
SWEDEN WITH A GOAL IN THE 99TH
NU TO PUNCH THEIR TICKET TO
THE FINALS.
THE GOOD NEWS FOR TEAM USA,
COCAPTAIN MAKING SAYS THAT SHE
WILL BE READY TO GO ON SUNDAY
AFTER MISSING SEMI FINALS
AGAINST ENGLAND.
>>> IT IS THE LARGEST FLYING
DISPLAY OF THE STARS AND
STRIPES IN THE NATION.
THE PNC AMERICAN FLAG BULLET
WAS INFLATED THIS MORNING IN
NEW JERSEY.
ALL IN CELEBRATION OF
INDEPENDENCE DAY BRICK THAT HOT
AIR BALLOON IS FIVE STORIES
TALL, A PILOT FROM PENNSYLVANIA
TREATED IT AFTER THE ATTACKS ON
9/11.
THE BALLOON IS FLOWN AT A NEW
YORK CITY AREA EVERY YEAR SINCE
THEN.
THAT IS SO ENORMOUS.
>>Steve: REALLY BIG.
>>Lindsey: KEPT HAVE PERFECT
WEATHER FOR THAT, TOO.
>>Steve: FOR THEM YES BUT TODAY
YOU DON'T WANT TO FLY A HOT AIR
BALLOON PUT A LOT TO TALK ABOUT
MOVING TO THE AFTERNOON HOURS
AND CROWDS ARE BEGINNING TO
BUILD HEAT EMERGENCY FOR THE
DISTRICT.
STAY HYDRATED AND THE BEST NEWS
OF ALL, COOLING CENTERS ARE
OPEN IN THE DISTRICT FOR THOSE
WITHOUT THE AC.
THIS IS OUR SKAB SEVEN
SHOWING NORTHWEST D.C.. YOU CAN
SEE THE CLOUDS BEGIN TO MOVE
IN.
THESE CLOUDS WILL EVENTUALLY
PRODUCE HEAVIER AMOUNTS OF RAIN
AS WE MOVED TO THE AFTERNOON
HOURS AND THAT IS WHAT WE HAVE
A FLASH FLOOD WATCH FOR PARTS
OF THE AREA.
A LIVE IN FEAR RIGHT NOW AND
THERE ARE THE CLOUDS AND WE
WILL KEEP CLOUDS IN PLACE WITH
THE TITLE BASIN LOOKING QUIET
FOR RIGHT NOW.
WE NOTE THOSE CROWDS WILL
DEFINITELY BUILD.
THE CAMERA ATOP THE WATERGATE
IS LOOKING GOOD RIGHT NOW.
ALTHOUGH IT IS ON THE HOT AND
HUMID SIDE.
80 DEGREES AT REAGAN NATIONAL
THIS ARE AND 80 LEESBURG, 85 IN
WARRENTON AND 85 IN
FREDERICKSBURG.
I DO WANT TO SHOW YOU THE FEELS
LIKE TEMPERATURES WELL INTO THE
MIDDLE TO UPPER 90S.
INSIDE AND AROUND THE BELTWAY
IT REALLY FEELS LIKE 104
DEGREES OVER IN ANNAPOLIS.
STORMWATCH 7 SATELLITE AND
RADAR SHOWS A FEW SHOWERS
DEVELOPING IN NORTHERN, COUNTY
WITH HEAVY DOWNPOURS INSIDE THE
CAPITAL BELTWAY.
HEAD OFF TO THE CHILL IN AREA
NEAR LAUREL AND BOWIE AND THAT
IS WHERE YOU ARE LOOKING AT A
FEW SHOWERS RIGHT NOW.
THE SHOWERS AND HEAVY DOWNPOURS
WILL BECOME MORE PROLIFIC
MOVING TO THE AFOON HOURS.
HERE IS THE LATEST FOR YOU ON
THE FLASH FLOOD WATCH FOR THE
DISTRICT, ARLINGTON, ALEXANDRIA
AND ALSO FAIRFAX AND PRINCE
WILLIAM, PARTS OF LOUDON,
MONTGOMERY AND PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY.
THAT IS UNTIL 8:00 P.M.
TONIGHT.
THE ALL-IMPORTANT FUTURECAST.
THIS IS OUR HIGH-RESOLUTION
MODEL AND LOOK AT THE HEAVY
RAIN FORECAST AT 2:00 P.M. THIS
AFTERNOON.
WE, COUNTY INTO PRINCE GEORGE'S
OVER TOWARD ANDREWS AND AS WE
HEAD THROUGH THE 3:00 HOUR,
ONCE AGAIN, THE POTENTIAL FOR
TORRENTIAL DOWNPOURS IN THE
DISTRICT OVER TOWARD NORTHEAST
AND UPPER NORTHWEST D.C. AND
THEN WE DO IT ALL OVER AGAIN
FOR THE 5:00 AND 6:00 HOUR
BEFORE THINGS START TO SETTLE
DOWN JUST A LITTLE BIT.
SOME OF THE SLOW-MOVING STORMS
ARE CAPABLE OF PRODUCING
UPWARDS OF TWO INCHES OF RAIN
OVER RELATIVELY SHORT PERIOD OF
TIME.
BY 11:00 P.M. TONIGHT, LITTLE
BIT OF PATCHY FOG BUT MOST OF
THE STORMS ARE OUT OF HERE.
HERE IS YOUR FOURTH OF JULY
OUTLOOK AS A MOVIE THIS
AFTERNOON.
STAY WEATHER ALERT AND TENDERS
WILL BE IN THE LOWER 90S AND
FEELS LIKE TEMPERATURE IS EVEN
HOTTER THAN THAT WITH FEELS
LIKE TEMPERATURES UPPER 90S TO
NEAR 100 DEGREES WITH WE CAN
TOMORROW MORNING IT IS HOT AND
SOUPY ONCE AGAIN.
TEMPERATURES THAT WILL BE IN
THE 70S AND HIGHS TOMORROW WILL
EVENTUALLY MAKE IT INTO THE
UPPER 80S TO AROUND 90 DEGREES
BUT UNSETTLED AGAIN TOMORROW.
GRAB THE UMBRELLA AS HE HAD
OUTDOORS AND AS ALWAYS, DOWN
LOADING YOUR STORM WATCH 7
WEATHER APP OR HAVE IT READY TO
GO.
IT WILL COME IN GREAT USE LATER
ON THIS AFTERNOON, ESPECIALLY
IF YOU ARE GOING TO FIND THAT
PERFECT PLACE TO WATCH THE
FIREWORKS.
NOT ONLY AT THE NATIONAL MALL
BUT THROUGHOUT THE AREA.
HERE'S YOUR 7 DAY OUTLOOK,
LINDSAY.
WE HAVE TEMPERATURES AT OR
ABOVE 90 DEGREES TOMORROW AND
SATURDAY AND THEN A LITTLE BIT
OF A COOL DOWN.
TO PIN POINT EXACTLY WHO WAS IN
THE HEAVIEST OF RAIN, OUR
MODELS DO A PRETTY GOOD JOB IN
SHOWING THAT OVER THE DISTRICT,
ARLINGTON AND ALEXANDRIA,
MOVING THROUGH EARLY TO MID
AFTERNOON AND EARLY EVENING
HOURS.
FINGERS CROSSED AT 9:07 PM
TONIGHT WE WILL HAVE ALL OF
THIS OUT OF HERE.
MY OTHER CONCERN IS A LOW CLOUD
DECK WITH YEARS AGO WE HAD THE
FIREWORKS AND WOULD'VE BEEN
BEAUTIFUL BUT WHEN THEY SHUT UP
THEY DISAPPEARED ALWAYS SOBER
FLASHES BUT IT COULD HAPPEN
AGAIN THIS YEAR.
>>Lindsey: HOPEFULLY, I WILL BE
AN OPTIMIST AND SAY FINGERS
CROSSED, HOPEFULLY EVERYTHING
WILL GO ACCORDING TO PLAN.
NEXT AT 7 IS UNDERSIDE WITH THE
HEALTH ALERT ABOUT SUNSCREEN.
ALL OF YOU HEADED TO THE BEACH
THIS FOURTH OF JULY.
>>Lindsey: WE ARE BA WITH A
HEALTH ALERT AS FAMILIES HEAD
TO THE BEACHES INDEPENDENCE
DAY.
WE HAVE GOT ANOTHER REMINDER ON
HOW IMPORTANT SUNSCREEN IS.
PARENTS, IF YOU DO NOT REMIND
YOUR KIDS, ODDS ARE THEY MAY
NOT BE PUTTING IT ON AT ALL BUT
AND WHEN THEY DID, ARE THEY
APPLYING ENOUGH?
BECKY REALLY HAS THE
EYE-OPENING SUNSCREEN
EXPERIMENT.
>> YOU KNOW HOW KIDS FEEL ABOUT
SUNSCREEN?
THEY HATE IT.
>> I DON'T WANT SUNSCREEN ON.
>> I DON'T NEED IT.> I GET
ANNOYED.
>> SUNSCREEN IS A KEEP IT.
>> IT IS QUITE ANNOYING.
>> PARENTS KNOW IT IS A MUST.
THE ONE BLISTERING SUMMER IS
EXTERIOR TO LIVE LIFE SOME
CANCERS WITH MULTISTATE ALL
SKIN TONES SHOULD WEAR
SUNSCREEN REGULARLY, PAST
RESEARCH SHOWS FOR INTENT DO
NOT.
WHY?
I SUBMIT THIS REENACTMENT FROM
MY DAUGHTER.
>> PUT ON SUNSCREEN.
>> NO, I DON'T WANT TO PUT ON
SUNSCREEN!
>> IT IS A BATTLE.
HOLLY, A FORMER ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL TEACHER AND FOUNDER OF
HER OWN SUNSCREEN COMPANY,
SUPER GRP YSTHERE IS AN
ALTERNATIVE.
>> IF YOU ARE OLD ENOUGH TO
BRUSH HER TEETH, AND WASH HER
HANDS, YOU ARE OLD ENOUGH TO DO
YOUR OWN SUNSCREEN.
>> REALLY?
LET'S TRY IT.
WE ARE USING A SPECIAL CAMERA
FITTED WITH A YOU BE SPENCER.
WHEN SOMETHING GOES ON IT SHOWS
THAT IT IS BLACK AND HOW IS ANY
MISSED SPOTS.
WE START WITH b,79 TO SEE IF TH
APPLICATION IS THOROUGH.
BECAUSE PUT IT ON AND IT WILL
REVIEW WHAT THEY MISSED.
>> AS EACH OF THESE CHILDREN
APPLIED, NONE OF THEM HIT THE
YEARS AND THE YEARS ARE
ACTUALLY VERY VULNERABLE TO SUN
DAMAGE.
>> AND OTHER FREQUENT MISS.
>> ILDREN FORGET TO PUT IT
RIGHT ON INTO THE HAIRLINE.
>> SOMETHING ALL THE YOUNGER
KIDS STRUGGLED WITH, NOT USING
ENOUGH SUNSCREEN.
>> WHAT YOU SEE?
>> I MISSED A LOT OF SPOTS.
>> SHE SAID THEY CAN KIDS ARE
AFRAID OF GETTING SUNSCREEN IN
THEIR MOUTH OR EYES BUT.
>> WE ARE MISSING A FEW
CRITICAL SPOTS RIGHT AROUND THE
EYE AREA WHICH IS OFTEN WHERE
SUN DAMAGE IS FIRST DETECTED
FROM AN AGING AND SKIN CANCER
PERSPECTIVE.
>> A STUDY SHOWED KIDS USING
ONE QUARTER OF THE AMOUNT OF
SUNSCREEN NEEDED TO GET THE
MUCH PROTECTION LIST ON THE
BOTTLE.OVING TO THE OLDER
GROUP OF 11 TO 12-YEAR-OLD, THE
DEPUTY THEY WERE MUCH MORE
CONSISTENT.
DEVON IS A LOT OF SUNSCREEN AND
ALSO GUSTS, ALSO AN 11-YEAR-OLD
WHO SEEM TO GET THE WATER.
>> I FEEL LIKE A TRY TO AVOID
IT BUT I SHOULDN'T. HAD A
GRANDFATHER WITH SKIN CANCER
AND I SHOULD TRY TO PREVENT
THAT.
>> HOLLY SAYS HE IS DOING IT
RIGHT.
>> USE IT ENOUGH SO THAT YOU
APPLY IT AND CAN SEE IT ON YOUR
SKIN AND THEN RUB IT IN AND HE
CANNOT SEE IT.
>> ALL THE KIDS THAT THEY
LEARNED A LOT AND TO TAKE WITH,
START THEM YOUNG BUT KIDS 10
AND UNDER NEED A LOT OF
COACHING TO GET ALL OF THE
PRODUCTION
>>Lindsey: I USE THE SPRAY
STUFF.
ADULTS DON'T LIKE IT THAT MUCH
EITHER.
RIGHT NOW
>>Lindsey: WELCOME BACK AND WE
ARE TO WHAT THE WEATHER AND IS
THE RAIN WERE KEEPING AN EYE
ON.
>>Steve: YES.
SLOW-MOING CLUSTERS OF WET
WEATHER THAT COULD BRING HEAVY
DOWNPOURS.
THAT IS WHAT WE HAVE A FLASH
FLOOD WATCH THE AREAS SHADED IN
GREEN.
MORE IMPORTANT, THE DISTRICT,
ARLINGTON IN ALEXANDRIA AND
SOME OF PEOPLE TRYING TO FIND
THAT PERFECT PLACE TRYING TO
FIND THE PERFECT FIREWORKS THIS
EVENING.
THIS IS WHAT WE EXPECT FOR
TERMS OF THIS EVENING.
WE ARE CALLING FOR TEMPERATURES
THAT WILL BE ON THE HOT SIDE
AND THEN BY 2:00 P.M. THIS
AFTERNOON, LOOK AT HOW THE
AREAS OF EUROS AND ORANGES AND
REDS BEGIN TO POP UP ON THE
SCREEN.
3:00 AND I WILL STOP THIS AT
4:00 AND 5:00 A LITTLE BIT OF A
LITTLE.
KEEP IN MIND, THIS IS JUST A
COMPUTER SIMULATION.
THESE MAYBE OFUR OR FIVE
MILES AND THE BIG PICTURE, THAT
IS NOT A LOT.
BUT YOU CAN MAKE A HUGE
DIFFERENCE WHETHER IT IS OVER
THE DISTRICT OR IT IS IN
NORTHERN MACOMB COUNTY OR
OTHERS.
IF ONE HAS A GOOD CHANCE OF
HEAVY RAIN MOVING TO THE
AFTERNOON INTO THE EVENING
HOURS.
>>Lindsey: IS EVERYONE GOING TO
BE AFFECTED OR POSSIBLY JUST
SOME PEOPLE IN WE DO NOT KNOW
EXACTLY WHERE?>Steve: WE
DON'T KNOW EXACTLY WHERE PRETTY
MUCH AT THIS POINT.
I WISH I HAD BETTER NEWS FOR.
>>Lindsey: WE WILL KEEP
TRACKING IT FOR YOU AND OF
COURSE WE HAVE THE APIS WILL
SEE CAN WATCH THE RADAR ALONG
WITH STEVE.
WE WILL BE BACK AFTER THIS.
>> NOW ABC7 NEWS AT NOON.
ON YOUR SIDE.
>>Lindsey: AMERICANS ARE READY
TO CELEBRATE THE INDEPENDENCE
DAY HOLIDAY IN A VARIETY OF
WAYS BUT BARBECUES TO
FIREWORKS.
MEANWHILE, OFFICIALS AND CITIES
ACROSS THE NATION ARE TAKING
PRECAUTIONS TO KEEP THEIR LARGE
GATHERINGS SAFE AND SECURE.
KAREN K FOR IS ON CONEY ISLAND
AND IN NEW YORK THAT IS WHERE
THEY ARE GEARING UP FOR THE BIG
DAY THAT IS ONLY UNDERWAY.
>>Reporter: ON THE NATIONAL
LEVEL, FEDERAL AGENCIES SAY NO
SPECIFIC CREDIBLE THREATS
AGAINST THE HOLIDAY BUT LAW
ENFORCEMENT WILL REMAIN
VIGILANT.
WHETHER SAID THE MAJOR
CELEBRATIONS LIKE HERE IN NEW
YORK DOWN IN D.C. OR ONE OF THE
SMALLER CELEBRATIONS TAKING
PLACE ACROSS THE COUNTRY TODAY.
INDEPENDENCE DAY CELEBRATIONS
SET ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND AAA
FORECAST NEARLY 49 MILLION
AMERICANS MAKING A GETAWAY TO
CELEBRATE.
>> UNEMPLOYMENT IS LOW,
AMERICANS HAVE ADDITIONAL
DISPOSABLE INCOME AND THEY TAKE
THE ADDITIONAL MONEY AND
PUTTING IT TOWARDS A TRIP WITH
FRIENDS AND FAMILY THIS YEAR.
>> IN WASHINGTON PRESIDENT
TRUMP WILL DELIVER A SPEECH AT
THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL.
IN ADDITION TO THE TRADITIONAL
FIREWORKS OF THE NATIONAL MALL.
FOR THE MASSIVE FIREWORKS
DISPLAY HERE IN NEW YORK, PRIME
VIEWING SPOTS WILL BE UNDER THE
EYE OF THE NYPD WITH PATROLS IN
THE AIR AND ON THE WATERWAYS.
CROWD SAFETY MEASURES WILL
INCLUDE BACKTRACKS AND
THOUSANDS OF OFFICERS ON DUTY.
>> THIS IS WHAT THE NYPD DOES.
WE HAVE SO MANY LARGE EVENTS
THROUGHOUT THE YEAR AND WE WILL
BE READY AND READY -- WHEN YOU
COME DOWN IT WILL BE A GREAT
SHOW.
>> THE NATIONAL RETAIL
FEDERATION AS MS. THAT
AMERICANS WILL SPEND $7.6
BILLION ON BARBECUES BUT HERE
CONEY ISLAND THEY WILL TAKE
THINGS FURTHER.
AT THE CORNER OF SURFACE TO
WILL ADMIT, CROSS WILL GATHER
FOR THE ANNUAL NATHAN'S HOT DOG
EATING CONTEST WITH WATCHING
COMPETITORS.
CONTESTANTS HAVE 10 MINUTES TO
DOWN AS MANY HOT DOGS AND BUNS
AS THEY CAN.
RAINING MEN'S CHAMPION JOEY
CHESTNUT HAS ONE CUP IS THE
LAST 10 OF 11 YEARS.
LAST YEAR HE SET A RECORD OF 74
HOT DOGS BUT THAT IS ONLY A
FRACTION OF THE AMOUNT THAT
AMERICANS ARE EXPECTED TO EAT
TODAY.
>>Lindsey: NOW TO OUR WEATHER.
STEVE.
IT IS LOOKING PRETTY CALM OUT
THERE RIGHT NOW BUT THERE ARE
STORMS APPROPRIATE WE CAN JUST
ONLY HOPE THAT IT WILL NOT RAIN
ON ANYONE'S PARADE AND WE
LISTEN TO THE LIVE MUSIC.
WE WANT THEM TO BE DRIVE-BY
THEY PERFORM.
>>Steve:PROPORTIONALLY
ESTIMATED THE MID AFTERNOON
HOURS INTO THE EARLY EVENING,
IT IS GOING TO GET WET AROUND
HERE.
TO PINPOINT EXACTLY WHO WILL
SEE THE HEAVIEST RAIN , THE
BEST CHANCES WILL BE INSIDE AND
AROUND THE CAPITAL BELTWAY.
AS YOU ALREADY HAVE A FLASH
FLOOD WATCH AS HE POSTED
STARTING AT 1:00 P.M. THIS
AFTERNOON AND EXTENDING UNTIL
8:00 P.M. TONIGHT.
STORM WATCH 7 SATELLITE AND
RADAR AND WHAT IS GOING ON
RIGHT NOW WITH A FEW SHOWERS
BEGIN TO ERUPT NORTH AND EAST
OF TOWN.
NOTHING THAT ISTERRIBLY HEAVY
IN THAT HAS TWO FREDERICK
COUNTY AND MACOMB COUNTY BORDER
OF TOWARD URBAN AND NORTH OF
GAITHERSBURG.
IN A BIT OF THUNDER AND
LIGHTNING RIGHT NOW.
HERE IS THE LATEST FOR YOU ON
OUR FUTURECAST AND THAT IS JUST
UPDATED FOR US.
NOTICE THE SHOWERS,
THUNDERSTORMS BEGIN TO POP UP
AS WE HEADED THROUGH THE 2:00
HOUR .
COMING MORE NUMEROUS AND HEAVY
AS WE HEADED TO THE 4:00 HOUR.
BY 6:00 P.M. WE COULD BE
LOOKING AT A HEAVIER SALE OVER
MANASSAS OVER TO FAIRFAX AND
WHETHER OR NOT THAT MOVES OVER
THE DISTRICT OR JUST POURS
ITSELF OUT, IT IS STILL YET TO
BE DETERMINED.
LET'S TALK ABOUT TEMPERATURES
RIGHT NOW BUT 80 DEGREES AT
REAGAN NATIONAL BUT THAT IS
JUST PART OF THE STORY.
WE FEEL LIKE THE MIDDLE TO
UPPER 90S TO CLOSE TO 100
DEGREES.
COMING UP IN A FEW MINUTES WE
WILL SHOW YOU FUTURECAST ONE
MORE TIME.
PLUS, WE ARE LOOKING AHEAD TO
THE FIREWORKS TONIGHT.
THEN THE UPCOMING WEEKEND.
ALL OF THAT AND MUCH MORE
COMING UP.
>>Lindsey: THANK YOU STEVE.
THIS FOURTH OF JULY ABC WANTS
TO HONOR A TRUE AMERICAN HERO.
A PILOT WHO FLEW MORE THAN 400
MISSIONS IN THREE DIFFERENT
WARS BUT IT IS A STORY THAT IS
VERY CLOSE TO ROBIN ROBERTS
HEART BECAUSE OF HER OWN FAMILY
LEGACY.
>> ON THIS JULY 4TH WE ARE
GIVEN THE OPPORTUNITY TO
REFLECT ON OUR RICH HISTORY AND
THOSE WHO HAVE SERVED OUR
COUNTRY.
HE PROTECTED AND FOUGHT FOR OUR
FREEDOM, THE FREEDOM THAT WE
ENJOY TO THIS DAY.
NO ONE BETTER SUPERVISED THE
SENTIMENT THAT A TRUE AMERICAN
PATRIOT.
BRONZE STORE WORLD WAR II
VETERAN COLONEL CHARLES McGEE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU FOR SERVING.
>> 30 YEARS IN THE AIR FORCE
WITH 409 MISSIONS AND 99 YEARS
YOUNG, COLONEL CHARLES McGEE IS
AN AMERICAN HERO.
WHEREVER HE GOES IN HIS ICONIC
TUSKEGEE AIRMEN RED BLAZER, ALL
EYES ARE ON HIM.
>> THANK YOU FOR YOUR SERVICES.
>> I APPRECIATE THAT.
>> THE COLONEL, ONE OF THE
FIRST BLACK FIGHTER PILOTS THE
BATTLE THE ENEMY ABROAD AND
SEGREGATION BACK HOME.
>> BLACK AMERICAN, SECOND-CLASS
CITIZEN.
DIG DITCHES, DRIVE TRUCKS, COOK
FOOD, BUT TO ANYTHING
TECHNICAL, IT WAS IMPOSSIBLE.
>> BUT THE TUSKEGEE AIRMEN MADE
THIS IN THE IMPOSSIBLE POSSIBLE
BUT COMPLETING OVER 1200 COMBAT
MISSIONS DURING WORLD WAR II.
>> YOU MIGHT SAY THAT THE AIR
FORCE REALLY LED OUR COUNTRY
INTO PROVIDING EQUAL ACCESS AND
EQUAL OPPORTUNITY FOR ALL.
>> ON THIS DAY OF INDEPENDENCE,
COLONEL McKEE REMINDS US TO SET
ASIDE OUR DIFFERENCES AND STAND
UNITED AS A COUNTRY.
>> WE ARE ALL AMERICANS.
FOR ME, WHY WOULD I SAY
AFRICAN-AMERICAN.
ARE YOU GERMAN-AMERICAN?
THAT'S WHEN THE BIG CHALLENGES
OF TODAY TO RECOGNIZE ALL FOR
WHO THEY ARE AND WHAT THEY DO
AND HOW THEY CARRY THEMSELVES
AND SUPPORT OUR COUNTRY.
>> KEEP IT GOOD YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU ARE THE FUTURE OF THE
COUNTRY.
>> I LOVE THAT AND THAT IS WHAT
I TRY TO PASS ON.
TO THE YOUNG FOLKS AS THEY
DEVELOP THEIR TALENT.
HOPEFULLY THEY PUT THEIR FINGER
ON SOMETHING THAT THEY ENJOY
DOING.
YOU REALIZE YOU HAVE TO REACH
OUT AND SHARE THIS EXPERIENCE
IS BUT WHEN PEOPLE ASK HOW ARE
THINGS, I SAY LIFE IS AMAZING.
>> THE TUSKEGEE AIRMEN ALSO
KNOWN AS THE RED TAILS AND I AM
AN HONORARY MEMBER THAT IS WHAT
I HAVE MY RED BLAZER.
I AM ALSO HONORED THAT I AM A
DAUGHTER OF A TUSKEGEE AIRMEN.
COLONEL LAWRENCE E ROBERTS.
AND LIKE COLONEL McKEE, HE
SHARED HIS SECRET TO SUCCESS
WITH HIS CHILDREN.
COLONEL McKEE'S OF THE 4P'S HE
CALLED THEM.
PROCEED, PREPARE, PERFORM AND
PERSEVERE.
IT SOUNDS A LOT LIKE MY DADDY.
MANY THINGS
>>Lindsey: WE ARE BACK IN WITH
A 15-YEAR-OLD PHENOM WHO
CONTINUES TO THE -- DOMINATE
UPON HIS PRICE RANGE BUT WE
HAVE MORE ON COCOAS LATEST
VEIN.
>> OVERNIGHT THIS TRADESHOW GOT
ANOTHER CHAPTER.
>> WITH HER POISE AND POWER
BEYOND HER YEARS COCO SAILED TO
THE THIRD OF WILMINGTON.
THE NEW SUNSHINE -- STAR SHINES
BRIGHTER.
>> HER VICTORY COMES TWO DAYS
AFTER THE AMERICAN TEEN
SENSATION ROCKED THE TENNIS
WORLD WITH A FIRST-ROUND
VICTORY OVER HER IDOL VENUS
WILLIAMS.
>> IT IS A DREAMY DEBUT FOR THE
13-YEAR-OLD.
>> THAT WERE MAKING HER INSTANT
START BRING THE PRAISE IN
APPROVAL OF SOME OF THE GREATS.
>> THERE SHE IS.
HOW IS EVERYTHING?
>> GOOD.
THANK YOU.
>> YOU GOT THAT ON CAMERA?
>> I COULD LIE AND SAY IT WAS
NOT HARD BUT IT WAS DEFINITELY
HARD TO RESET WITHOUT THIS BUZZ
GOING ON.
I WAS JUST TELLING MYSELF, IF
YOU WANT MORE MOST OF IT.
TO CONTINUE TO WORK HARD AND
STAY FOCUSED.
>> THE RESET SHE DID ON
WEDNESDAY DEFEATING HER
OPPONENT.
THE PACKED HOUSE AND HER PROUD
PARENTS ON THEIR FEET IN A
PRAYER OVATION.
>> SHE DID IT WITH SUCH
STOPPED.
>> EVERYTHING HAS JUST COME
TOGETHER.
I AM SO PROUD OF MY DAUGHTER.
WATCHING HER AND THE MATURITY
THAT SHE HAS DEVELOPED THIS
LAST WEEK AND AND A HALF IN TWO
WEEKS.
>> OPPOSITION WAS TO WIN THE
TOURNAMENT BUT REGARDLESS OF
THE OUTCOME FOR ME, WE ARTY
HAVE THE SUCCESS BUT WITH
COHERENCE AND GROWTH IN HER.
>> COCO IS THE YOUNGEST WOMAN
TO ADVANCE TO WILMINGTON'S
THIRD ROUND SINCE 1991 AND SHE
IS NOT INTIMIDATED.
>> I THINK I CAN BEAT ANYONE
WHO IS ACROSS THE COURT.
I DO NOT THINK I CAN WITH A
MATCH IN WILL NOT STEP IN THE
CORPORATE.
>>Lindsey: SHE IS ON THE TOP OF
HER GAME AND YOU ON THE TOP OF
YEARS BUT YOU ARE LOOKING FOR
BECAUSE THEY FIND TO COME.
>>Steve: WANT TO TALK ABOUT OUR
BY OUR ESTIMATE TO THE
AFTERNOON.
THIS IS SKYLAB SEVEN AND LOOK
AT THE BOAT TRAFFIC UP AND DOWN
THE POTOMAC WITH EVERY PATIENT
TO GET FROM POINT A TO POINT B.
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE THEY
LIVE YOU RIGHT NOW.HOWING
OUR SKIES ARE HAZY AND CLOUDY
BUT AT LEAST IT IS DRY INSIDE
THE CAPITAL BELTWAY.
OVER TOWARDS FRIENDSHIP HEIGHTS
AND CHEVY CHASE AND COSBY
--CONTINUE TO BUILD.
OUR NEXT STOP, THE TELEVISION
TRAFFIC BUT IT DOES NOT LOOK
BAD A LOT OF ROADWAYS ARE CLOSE
WOULD CHECK WITH WJLA.com FOR
THE LATEST TRAFFIC MAPS.
IT IS SEVEN MANASSES AND FEELS
LIKE TEMPERATURE IS ALREADY AT
100 IN LEESBURG AND FEELS LIKE
96 DEGREES AT REAGAN NATIONAL
AIRPORT WITH A HEAT EMERGENCY
FOR THE DISTRICT AND THAT MEANS
COOLING CENTERS ARE NOW OPEN
THROUGHOUT THE DISTRICT.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE AC OR YOU
NEED A PLACE TO TAKE A BREAK,
BUT AS WE NEED TO GO.
HEAT INDEX VALUES THROUGHOUT
THE AFTERNOON AND WANT TO THE
90S WITH SOME IS HEAVIER
DOWNPOURS WILL CLOSED DOWN BUT
IT WILL STILL STAYS TOGETHER.
MOVING THROUGH THIS AFTERNOON
AND INTO THE EVENING.
STORMWATCH 7 SATELLITE AND
RADAR A LOOK AT THE SHOWERS AND
HEAVY RAIN ALREADY BEGINNING TO
BLOSSOM.
NORTH OF GAITHERSBURG UP TOWARD
URBANA AND BURNSVILLE AND
DAMASCUS ALL LOOKING AT WET
WEATHER RIGHT NOW.
THE SAME FOR LANHAM.
NOTHING THAT IS SEVERE BUT SLOW
MOVING STORMS CAPABLE OF
PRODUCING VERY HEAVY RAIN OVER
SHORT PERIOD OF TIME.
ALSO, THE POTENTIAL FOR
LOCALIZED FLASH FLOODING.
FLASH FLOOD WATCH GOES INTO
EFFECT AT 1:00 THIS AFTERNOON
UNTIL 8:00 TONIGHT.
ALL THE AREAS THAT ARE SHADED
IN GREEN.
HERE IS OUR FUTURECAST AND ALSO
THIS WEEK HOUR BY HOUR AND
MOVING DO THIS AFTERNOON AND
EVENING.
NOTICE THE WET WEATHER DEVELOPS
AT 2:00, 3:00 AND NORTH AND
EAST OF D.C.. THE EASTERN EDGE
OF THE CAPITAL BELTWAY MOVING
INTO THE 4:00 HOUR AND A LITTLE
BIT AVAILABLE, AT LEAST FOR THE
DISTRICT.
BY 5:00 P.M. WE COULD BE
LOOKING AT HEAVIER GRAINS JUST
OFF TOWARD THE SOUTH AND WEST
OF US.
THE BIG QUESTION MARK, WHERE
WITH THE STORMS SET UP EXACTLY?
WILL IT BE OVER THE DISTRICT OR
FAIRFAX AND IS AND WAS GUESS AT
THIS POINT.
YOU ARE GOING INTO THE NATIONAL
MALL WE SHOULD HAVE A SECURE
PLACE TO GO SHOULD YOU FIND
SOME IS HEAVIER DOWNPOURS
OVERHEAD.HERE IS ANY GOOD
NEWS OF THIS FORECAST, MOVING
INTO THE 9:00 HOUR, THE
HEAVIEST OF RAIN BEGINS TO
DIMINISH AND THE CHANCES OF
HEAVIER RAIN WILL BEGIN TO EASE
BUT BY 11:00 P.M. TONIGHT A LOT
OF FOLKS GOING HOME AND THINGS
SHOULD BEGIN TO IMPROVE EVEN
THOUGH WE MIGHT SEE A BIT OF
PATCHY FOG.
FOR THIS AFTERNOON AND INTO THE
EVENING FOR FIREWORKS, THE
TEMPERATURES WILL BE IN THE
80S.
WAKING UP EARLY TOMORROW
MORNING WITH TEMPERATURES IN
THE 70S AND ONCE AGAIN, VERY
WARM AND VERY HUMID.
HIGHS TOMORROW MAKE INTO THE
MID TO UPPER 80S TO CLOSE TO 90
DEGREES.
WE ARE LOOKING AT YET ANOTHER
ROUND OF WET WEATHER TO THE
AFTERNOON HOURS.
SEVEN DAY OUTLOOK FROM STORM
WATCH 7 AND 91 ON SATURDAY AND
A SEVEN ON SUNDAY AND WE DROVE
DOWN TO THE 80S EARLY NEXT
WEEK.
>>Lindsey: SEVEN IS ON THE SIDE
WITH A SUMMER HOLIDAY WARNING.
ACCORDING TO THE CDC, DROWNING
IS THE LEADING CAUSE OF
UNINTENTIONAL DEATHS IN
CHILDREN AGES 1 TO 4. BEFORE
YOU HEAD TO THE POOL OR THE
BEACHES WILL BE THE FOURTH, GIO
BENITEZ IS TAKING LOOK ON HOW
TO KEEP HER FAMILY SAFE.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE ANY OTHER
SUMMER POOL PARTY PRETTY YOUNG
PEOPLE SPLASHING IN THE WATER.
PARENTS ENJOYING THE BARBECUE.
SOMEWHERE IN THIS POOL, FIVE
DIFFERENT SWIMMERS ARE ABOUT TO
SIMULATE THAT THEY ARE
DROWNING.
WE ARE WONDERING IF THESE MOMS
AND DADS CAN SPOT THEM.
DROWNING CAN HAPPEN IN JUST
SECONDS AND IS OFTEN DIFFICULT
TO SPOT.
IT IS HAPPENING TO SOMEONE IN
THIS PUBLIC POOL RIGHT NOW.
CAN YOU SPOT IT?
THERE SHE IS.
FORTUNATELY, IF LIFEGUARDS
SPONSOR IT MAKES THE RESCUE.
IT IS IN RESIDENTIAL POOLS WERE
LIFEGUARDS ARE NOT USUALLY
PRESENT THAT THE MAJORITY OF
DRAWINGS TAKE PLACE.
SAFETY EXPERTS SAY THAT PART OF
THE REASON IS DISTRACTED
PARENTS.
TALKING ON THEIR PHONES,
GRILLING, SOCIALIZING AND
SUPERVISING OTHER CHILDREN WITH
NO WATER WATCH.
A PERSON WITH EYES ON THE WATER
AT ALL TIMES.E INVITED THIS
GROUP OF PARENTS TO A POOL
PARTY AND ASSIGNING THEM TASKS
LIKE RUNNING THAT GRILL WITH OF
COURSE, TENDING TO THEIR OWN
YOUNG KIDS.
WE'VE ALSO ADDED SWIMMERS
SPLASH IN THE PULPIT BUT THOSE
SWIMMERS ARE ACTUALLY TRAINED
LIFEGUARDS AND SOME INSTRUCTORS
SKILLED IN MIMICKING A
DROWNING.
THE PARENTS KNOW THEY ARE HERE
TO LEARN ABOUT WATER SAFETY
WITH SOME SORT OF DEMONSTRATION
BEGINNING IN ABOUT AN HOUR.
BUT SINCE DROWNING OFTEN
HAPPENS WHEN YOU LEAST EXPECT
IT WILL BEGIN RIGHT NOW.
WITH CAMERAS ROLLING I WATCH
FROM A GARAGE JUST NEXT TO THE
PULPIT OBSERVING SOME PARENTS
CHECK IN THE WATER, BUT MOSTLY
THEY ARE FOCUSED ON THEIR
ASSIGNMENTS IN THE PARTY.
AFTER 30 MINUTES, THERE WE GO.
SHE WENT UNDER.
OUR SWIM INSTRUCTOR SIMILES A
DROWNING.
STRUGGLING TO KEEP HER HEAD
ABOVE WATER.
ARMS CALLING FOR THE SURFACE.
JUST LIKE THE REAL THING, SHE
BARELY MAKES A SOUND.
MEANWHILE, OUR GUESTS SEEM NOT
TO NOTICE BIT MORE THAN A
MINUTE GOES BY.
>> SHE IS STILL STRUGGLING AND
NOBODY IS LOOKING.
WE ARE NOW LOOKING AT MORE THAN
2 AND A HALF MINUTES AND STILL
NOBODY NOTICES A THING.
>> AFTER MORE THAN FOUR MINUTES
SHE SALUTES A WORST-CASE
SCENARIO AND STOPS MOVING.
SHE IS A TRAINED PROFESSIONAL
AND IS JUST ACTING.
JOSH FROM THE AMERICAN RED
CROSS HAS BEEN WATCHING WITH
US.
>> FOREIGN HAVE MINUTES AND
STILL NO PARENTS NOTICED
ANYTHIN.
>> RIGHT.
>> DOES THAT SURPRISE YOU?
>> IT DOES NOT.
>> KELLY GOES BACK TO SWIMMING
AND WE QUEUE ANOTHER SUMMER AND
ANOTHER.ND ANOTHER.
ALL MIMICKING A JOURNEY BUT
NOBODY STEPS IN.
>> YOU DO NOT REALIZE HOW
COMPLETE THESE CUTTINGS AND GO
FROM A FUN POOL PARTY TO AN
INCIDENT WHERE SOMEONE NEEDS
HELP.> NOW THE KIDS ARE
GOING TO GET OUT OF THE WATER
AND THEY WILL GET SOME SNACKS
AND THEY LEAVE SOMEONE BEHIND.
THAT PERSON IS GOING TO START
TO DROWN.
>> AFTER 30 SECONDS A
PURPOSEFUL STRUGGLE, THAT IS
THAT SPONSOR.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> WITHIN 36 SECONDS HE
NOTICED.
>> WE HOPE YOU WILL NOTICE
FASTER.
>> IN SOME CASES SWIMMERS CAN
SUBMERGE IN JUST A FEW SECONDS
MAKING THEM HARD TO SPOT.
>> THERE WERE FOUR DROWNINGS
THE NEW BASEBALL IT.
HOW TO MAKE YOU FEEL?
>> MAKERS FROM THE DECK SO TURN
MY BACK WITH THAT DOES NOT MEAN
OTHER KIDS ARE IN THE PULPIT.
>> I GOT THROWN OFF BY THEIR
AGE BUT WE TOOK FOR GRANTED
THAT THEY COULD ALL SWIM.
>> FOR THE MAN WHO SPOTTED THE
VICTIM IT WAS SO CLOSE TO
REALITY.
>> WHILE WE SO NERVOUS?
YOU WERE VISIBLY SHAKEN.
>> IT DID HAPPEN TO MY CHILD.
>> HIS DAUGHTER SURVIVED BUT
WHEN SHE WAS JUST THREE SHE
BEGAN DROWNING IN A HOT TUB.
SHE--HE WAS ON THE PHONE.
>> I GOT A PHONE CALL AND A
DISTRACTED AND SHE WAS IN
TROUBLE.
THAT BROUGHT BACK MEMORIES.
>> ONE OF THE SOLUTIONS IS A
WATER WATER.
SOME WERE STANDING NEXT TO THE
POOL FREE FROM DISTRACTIONS AND
CONSTANTLY SCANNING THE WATER
FOR ANY SIGNS OF DISTRESS.
ROTATING EVERY 15 MINUTES TO
AVOID LOSING FOCUS.
WE SHOWED THE PARENTS WILL BE
>>Lindsey: INTO THE SPOTLIGHT
ON EDUCATION WE ARE TAKING A
CLOSER LOOK AT A PROGRAM
DESIGNED TO ENRICH STUDENTS AND
KEEP THEM PLUGGED INTO LEARNING
DURING THE SUMMER MONTHS.
KELLY LYNN IS TAKING US TO
NORTHWEST AT A LOOK AT THE
SUMMER DISCOVERY PROGRAM.
>> NAME THEM ONE BY ONE.
>> A JOURNEY TO SPACE AND
ENCOUNTER WITH HEROES AND
VILLAINS AND THE EXECUTION OF
SIMPLE MISSIONS.>> ON SIMPLE
MISSIONS AND WE ARE ARCHITECTS
AND ENGINEERS AND HEROES AND
VILLAINS.
WE LEARN TO DRAW AND WRITE OUR
COMMENTS BUT.
>> JUST A FEW THE ACTIVITIES
AND GAMES OVER TO THE D.C.
PUBLIC SCHOOLS SUMMER DISCOVERY
PROGRAM.
>> THEGOAL IS TO REDUCE SUMMER
LEARNING LOSS GIVE OUR SCHOLARS
ENRICHMENT OPPORTUNITIES ALL
SUMMER LONG.
>> LEARNING HOW TO DRAW .
>> LEARNING THAT COMES AT NO
CHARGE.
>> COULD WE SURVIVE IN SPACE?
>> NO.
>> AND IS OFFERED AT EIGHT
CAMPUSES ACROSS THE CITY DURING
THE MONTHS OF JUNE AND JULY.
>> FOR EVERY SCHOLAR THAT IS IN
THE SUMMER SCHOOL PROGRAM, WE
ALSO HAVE A SLOT IN THE
AFTERSCHOOL PROGRAM.
WE ARE OFFERING PROGRAM FROM
8:00 A.M. UNTIL 5:30 P.M..
>> FOR THIS NINE-YEAR-OLD, THE
STEM FOCUSED CONTENT ALLOWS HER
TO PURSUE SOME OF HER FAVORITE
ACTIVITIES.
>> I LIKE ENGINEERING AND
DESIGNING THINGS.
>> IN THE D.C. PS, SUMMER
DISCOVERY PROGRAM.
>> WE WILL START HERE TOMORROW.
>> ADHERES IN ELEMENTARY IN
NORTHWEST.
KELLY LYNN ABC 7 NEWS.
>>Lindsey: IF YOU KNOW SOMEONE
IN EDUCATION OR PROGRAM THAT
KELLY SHOULD BE SHINING THE
SPOTLIGHT ON WE WANT TO HEAR
FROM YOU.
GO TO WJLA.com/UNDERSIDE TO
SEND IN YOUR SUGGESTIONS.
STICK WITH US AND STEVE WILL BE
BACK WITH A FINAL CHECK ON THE
HOLIDAY FORECAST AFTER THE
BREAK.
>> THREE, TWO, ONE AND THEY ARE
OFF!
>>Lindsey: THE NATHAN'S DOG HOT
CONGRESS IS HAPPY RIGHT NOW BUT
LAST IN OUR AREA TO DIVISIONS
COMPETED IN THE PALISADES PIE
EATING CONTEST.HERE WAS A
KIDS CHALLENGE IN THE ONE FOR
THE ADULTS.T IS SO MUCH
CUTER WITH THE KIDS.
THE TWIST IS THAT THIS WAS,
OBVIOUSLY, HANDS-FREE THERE.
GOODNESS.
>>Steve: WHAT A MESS BUT A LOT
OF FUN.
I THINK I COULD DO BETTER IF IT
WAS CHOCOLATE CREAM OR COCONUT
CREAM AS OPPOSED TO A FRUIT
PIE.
>>Lindsey: I FEEL LIKE THE
CHERRIES ARE EASIER TO, YOU
KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW.
>>Steve: ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO
TO THE AFTERNOON HOURS AND WE
ARE LIVE NOW ALMOST AT 1:00.
WE HAVE A FLASH FLOOD WATCH
THAT WILL GO INTO EFFECT IN
ABOUT FOUR MINUTES UNTIL 8:00
P.M. TONIGHT.
AREAS SHADED IN GREEN.
HERE'S OUR FUTURE COST AT 2:00
AND NOTICE IS TO BE SEE THE
HEAVIEST OF THE DAMPERS ARE
UNDERWAY.
AS WITH THE 3:00 HOUR THE 4:00
HOUR, THIS IS OUR
HIGH-RESOLUTION MODEL AND IT
DOES KEEP THE HEAVIEST OF THE
RAIN, AT LEAST ACCORDING TO
THIS MODEL, OUTSIDE THE
BELTWAY.
HOWEVER, THIS COULD SHIFT A FEW
MILES AND AROUND HERE, THREE,
FOUR, FIVE, SIX MILES MAKES A
BIG DIFFERENCE.
AS YOU MOVE INTO THE 7:00 AND
8:00 HOURS, THINGS BEGIN TO
IMPROVE FOR THE FIREWORKS.
FOURTH OF JULY AFTERNOON AND
EVENING FORECAST LOOKS LIKE
THIS BUT IT IS HOT, IT IS HUMID
AND TEMPERATURES WILL INTO THE
UPPER 80S NEAR 90 TWO START.
HEAVY DOWNPOURS COULD BRING
UPWARDS OF TWO INCHES OF RAIN,
LOCALIZED FLOODING AND EVEN
SOME THUNDERSTORMS WITH GUSTY
WINDS.
WE WILL KEEP YOU UPDATED ALL
AFTERNOON RIGHT HERE ON