>> NOW, ABC 7 NEWS AT 6:30, ON
YOR SIDE.
WE BEGIN WITH A BREAKING NEWS
ALERT.
>> Anchor: THAT BREAKING NEWS, A
SCARE AT UNION STATION.
PASSENGERS FLEEING AFTER HEARING
WHAT THEY THOUGHT WERE GUNSHOTS.
VICTORIA SANCHEZ IS LIVE AT
TSUNAMI I DONUNION STATION.
VICTORIA, YOU SPOKE WITH
WITNESSES.
WHAT ARE THEY TELLING YOU?
>> CARL, THIS HAPPENED JUST
BEFORE 5 O'CLOCK WHEN SOMEONE
CALLED METRO POLICE TO SAY THIS
THEY HEARD GUNSHOTS AND WERE
AFRAID THAT THERE WAS AN ACTIVE
SHOOTER INSIDE UNION STATION.
LUCKILY, THAT WAS NOT THE CASE.
I SPOKE TO AMTRAK POLICE WHO
TELL ME THAT THEY WERE ACTUALLY
FIRE CRACKERS THAT JUVENILES SET
OFF.
THIS IS SOME VIDEO THAT WE GOT
JUST A LITTLE BIT AGO.
IT WAS A MUCH QUIETER SCENE THAN
WHAT SOME OF THE WITNESSES WERE
TELLING ME.
THEY SAID DOZENS OF PEOPLE RAN
FOR COVER.
ONE WOMAN ACTUALLY TWEETED THAT
SHE HID HERSELF IN A BATHROOM
ONCE SHE HEARD THOSE LOUD BANGS.
LUCKILY, SHE SAID THAT SHE CAME
OUT AND PEOPLE WERE CALM AFTER
IT WAS KNOWN THAT IT WAS NOT
GUNSHOTS BUT, IN FACT,
FIREWORKS.
I SPOKE TO A MOON WHO WAS
VISITING D.C. WITH HIS FAMILY
THIS WEEKEND ABOUT TO GET ON AN
AMTRAK TRAIN BACK TO NEW JERSEY.
THIS IS WHAT HE HAD TO SAY ABOUT
WHAT HE HEARD.
>> WALK THROUGH UNION STATION
AND SOMEONE SET OFF SOME
FIREWORKS.
>> AND WHAT DID IT SOUND LIKE TO
YOU?
>> IT SOUNDED VERY LOUD AND VERY
NOISY AND IT VERY MUCH COULD
HAVE BEEN GUNSHOTS.
I WAS NOT WAITING AROUND TO FIND
OUT WHAT IT WAS.
>> YOU ARE WITH YOUR FAMILY.
>> I WAS WITH MY FAMILY, YES.
>> HOW DOES THAT MAKE YOU FEEL
WHEN YOU HEAR SOMETHING LIKE
THAT?
>> IT IS VERY FRIGHTENING FOR
THEM.
MY DAUGHTERS WERE UPSET BY IT.
THEY DIDN'T REALLY UNDERSTAND
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
THEY JUST KNEW MOMMY AND DADDY
WERE SAYING TO RUN ALL THE
SUDDEN.
>> YOU CAN JUST IMAGINE WHAT
PEOPLE WERE FEELING LIKE WHEN
THEY ARE INSIDE UNION STATION,
ABOUT TO GET ON THEIR TRAINS
WHEN THEY HEARD THESE LOUD
BANGS.
PEOPLE SAID THIS THEY WERE GLAD
THIS WAS NOT A SHOOTING.
BUT STILL, AT THIS DAY AND AGE
WHEN YOU HEAR A SHOOTING LIKE
THIS, POSSIBLY HAPPENING, FIND
OUT IT IS FIREWORKS, HEARTS WERE
STILL POUNDING IS WHAT I AM
BEING TOLD.
AMTRAK POLICE, THEY ARE TAKING
THE LEAD ON THIS INVESTIGATION
BECAUSE IT DID HAPPEN AT UNION
STATION.
THEY SAY H THAT THE JUVENILES WO
SET OFF THE FIRE CRACKERS RAN
OUT A SIDE DOOR AND WERE NOT
CAUGHT.
VICTORIA SANCHEZ, ABC 7 NEWS.
>> Anchor: THANK YOU.
MORE BREAKING NEWS NOW.
WE NOW KNOW THE NAME OF THE MAN
POLICE SAY CAUSED A DEADLY WRONG
WAY CRASH.
26-YEAR-OLDMIGUEL GOMEZ.
THE 22-YEAR-OLD DRIVER
PRONOUNED DEAD ON THE SKI.
ALCOSCENE.
SCENE.
GOMEZ IS BEING TREATED FOR HIS
INJURIES.
>>> WE WILL, OF COURSE, CONTINUE
TO FOLLOW THESE BREAKING STORIES
AND BRING YOU NEW INFORMATION AS
SOON AS WE GET IT ON THE ABC 7
NEWS APP.
>>> AND TURNING TO WEATHER NOW
WHERE WE ARE FEELING A BIT
COOLER THAN YESTERDAY BUT DON'T
BE FOOLED.
YOU KNOW IF YOU HAVE BEEN OUT
SIDE, IT IS STILL VERY MUGGY.
LIVE LOOK AT STORM WATCH 7
RADAR.
FEW SHOWERS POPPING UP.
>>> WATCHING A FEW SHOWERS.
AS WE LOOK ACROSS OUR AREA,
BILLOWING CLOUDS, BAY BRIDGE
CAMERA I THOUGHT WAS BROKENFUL .
THERE'S A HEAVY SHOWER COMING
DOWN OBSCURING THE VIEW.
MID AND UPPER 80s.
MOST HUNG IN THE 80s.
IT FEELS THAT MUCH WARMER.
SO INTO THE EVENING, SOME
SCATTERED SHOWERS, COULD BE SOME
RUMBLES OF THUNDER DEEPER INTO
THE NIGHTTIME HOURS.
SOME COULD BE BIG RAINERS.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE A FLASH FLOOD
WATCH OUT FOR THE ENTIRE AREA.
NOT MUCH OUT THERE THAN A SPOTTY
SHOWER OR TWO.
SO COMING UP, WE WILL TIME OUT
THE SHOWER POTENTIAL FOR YOUR
MORNING RUSH ON MONDAY.
LOOK AT DRYER, MORE COMFORTABLE
AIR MOVING IN.
>> Anchor: THANK YOU.
LAST TIME IN NIGHT'S STORMS FORO
CLOSE THE JEFFERSON MEMORIAL
TODAY.
NO ONE WAS INJURED AND CLEANUP
IS EXPECTED TO WRAP UP BY THE
END OF THE DAY.
>>> AND ROUTE 50 IN LOWDEN
COUNTY BACK OPEN TONIGHT AFTER
THE STRONG STORMS SENT DOWN THIS
TREE CRASHING.
FOX CHASE FARM LANE.
YOU CAN SEE THE TREE BROUGHT
DOWN WIRES AS WELL.
ALL OF THIS HAD TO BE CLEARED
OUT SAFELY BEFORE THEY COULD LET
DRIVERS GET THROUGH AGAIN OF THE
BUT AGAIN THAT INTERSECTION IS
BACK OPEN TONIGHT.
>>> YOU CAN TRACK TODAY AS HOT
TEMPERATURES AND MONITOR THE
RADAR FOR ANY STORMS THAT MAY
COME.
DOWNLOAD THE STORM WATCH 7 APP.
>>> JOLTED BY TWO MAJOR
EARTHQUAKES, PEOPLE IN SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA ARE CAUTIOUSLY COMING
THROUGH THE DAMAGE AS THOUSANDS
OF AFTERSHOCKING CONTINUED TO
RATTLE THE REGION.
NEW VIDEO COMES IN SHOWING THE
POWER OF FRIDAY'S 7.1 MAGNITUDE
EARTHQUAKE.
IN THE SURVEILLANCE VIDEO, YOU
SEE THE CARS JUST SHAKING AND A
CAT RUNNING BY FRANTICALLY.
OUR SISTER STATION IN CALIFORNIA
IS FOLLOWING THE LATEST
DEVELOPMENTS FOR US.
>>> WALKING THROUGH RIDGECREST
NEIGHBORHOODS TODAY, IT IS NOT
THAT OBVIOUS THAT THIS COMMUNITY
WITH STOOD TWO MAJOR EARTHQUAKES
AND THOUSANDS OF AFTER SHOCKS.
TODAY FAMILIES ARE RETURNING
HOME FROM SHELTERS AND TENTS TO
GET THEIR HOUSES BACK IN ORDER.
BUT TURN A CORNER AND YOU WILL
SEE SIGHT LIKE THIS.
WHERE BRICK WALLS FELL APART AND
GIVES YOU PAUSE TO REMEMBER HOW
SCARY IT ALL WAS BUT MOST
IMPORTANTLY PEOPLE ARE NOW
GIVING THANKS THE DAMAGE WASN'T
ANY WORSE.
>> ANY TIME THAT WE CAN GO
THROUGH 7 POINT EARTHQUAKE AND
DO NOT REPORT A FATALITY, DO NOT
SUFFER STRAWRL D STRUCTURAL DAMT
WAS SIGNIFICANT, THAT'S A
MIRACLE.
>> IT'S BEEN OKAY.
THE WAY THEY BUILT THIS HOUSE IS
'83 STRUCTURALLY SOUND.
>> HE TOOK DOWN ALL THE PHOTOS
FROM HIS WALLS, BUT WHEN
FRIDAY'S 7.1 HIT, FURNITURE WENT
FLYING.
>> THIS WAS ON THAT PLACE OVER
THERE.  SO IT MOVED TOWARD THE
WALL.
IT GOT HUNG UP THERE.
>> NOW, HE AND HIS WIFE ARE
CLEANING UP.
AND JUST STARTING TO CALM DOWN.
REPORTING IN RIDGECREST, EMMA
GOSS.
>> Anchor: THIS WEEK, VIRGINIA
LAWMAKERS WILL RETURN TO
RICHMOND FOR WHAT IS EXPECTED TO
BE A CONTENTIOUS SPECIAL
SESSION.
GOVERNOR NORTHAM CALLED THE
SESSION TO CONSIDER GUN LAWS.
THE DEADLY SHOOTING AT VIRGINIA
BEACH LAST MONTH.
THE REPUBLICAN MAJORITY,
HOWEVER, SAYING THEY ARE LIKELY
TO FOCUS ON DIFFERENT ISSUES.
THAT SESSION SET TO BEGIN ON
TUESDAY.
>>> CELEBRATIONS UNDERWAY RIGHT
NOW AFTER THE U.S. WOMEN'S
NATIONAL TEAM WON ITS FOURTH
WORLD CUP BEATING THE NEGLECTER
NETHERLANDS 2-0.
>> LOOKING, CUTTING.
GOT IT.
THE U.S.
>> JUST THRILLING.
FANS WATCHING AROUND THE
COUNTRY, INCLUDING AT A FEW
WATCH PARTIES HERE.
WE SPOKE WITH FANS ABOUT WHY
THIS WIN MEANT SO MUCH.
>> WITH THE FINAL WHISTLE,
CELEBRATIONS ERUPTED ALL ACROSS
THE DMV AND RIGHT HERE AT
NATIONAL HARBOR WHERE HUNDREDS
WATCHED THE WOMEN'S NATIONAL
TEAM MARCH ON TO VICTORY.
NEXT GENERATION OF SOCCER STARS
WATCH THE U.S. WOMEN WHEN THEIR
FOURTH WORLD CUP.
COACH FINNEY SAYS THE STEAM'S
SWAGGER.
>>  HAVE LIT A FIRE.
>> THE GIRLS TALK ABOUT THE
GAMES, SHOWING MORE EMOTION.
>> AND WHAT A SIGHT IT WAS.
>> WE UNDERSTAND THAT THE EYES
ARE ON US AND IT HAS BEEN A MAG
AMAGNIFIED SITUATION.
>> THE SCALE OF THE
ACCOMPLISHMENT INSPIRING SO
MANY.
>> WATCHING THESE OLDER PLAYERS
MAKES ME WANT TO BE MORE LIKE
THEM WHEN I GROW UP.
>> IT INSPIRES ME BECAUSE I WANT
TO PLAY ON A PROFESSIONAL GLEEM
>> WITH PARADES ALREADY IN THE
PLANNING STAGES, PEOPLE HOPING
THE WOMEN'S PROGRAM GET ITS JUST
REWARDS.
>> SUPPORTS OUR WOMEN'S TEAM IN
THE FUTURE.
GIVE THEM WHAT THEY DESERVE ON
AND OFF THE FIELD.
>> GO USA.
>> GOES USA.
>> CONGRATULATIONS TO THEM.
COMING UP ON ABC 7 NEWS AT 6:30,
THE SEARCH FOR TWO AMERICANS
MISSING IN THE CARIBBEAN TAKING
A GRIZZLY TURN.
IT'S JUST BEEN FOUND AND WHAT
HAPPENS NEXT.
AND NEW APPROACH, WHAT
PROTESTERS IN HONG KONG WERE
DOING DIFFERENTLY TO RECRUIT
MORE SUPPORT.
>>> NEW NUMBERS ON THE JOB, THE
PRESIDENT'S JOB PERFORMANCE.
THE BIG GAINS HAS MADE.
THE ONE THING AMERICANS WANT TO
SEE IMPROVE THE MOST.
>> Anchor: THOUSANDS OF
PROTESTERS IN HONG KONG TRYING
TO REACH AND RECRUIT VISITORS
FROM MAINLAND CHINA.
THOUSANDS WALKED THROUGH A
POPULAR SHOPPING AREA.
PROTESTERS WERE STILL RALLYING
AGAINST CHINA'S ATTEMPTS TO
IMPOSE EXTRADITION LAW THAT MANY
FEAR WOULD CHIP AWAY AT HONG
KONG'S AUTONOMY.
>>> NEW DEVELOPMENTS FOR MISSING
TOURISTS IN BARBADOS.
THE JET SKI THEY RENTED HAS BEEN
FOUND.
FOUND OFF THE COAST.OF GUADALUP.
MISSING SINCE JUNE 24TH.
FRENCH AUTHORITIES SAY THERE WAS
NO SIGN OF THEM NEAR THE JET
SKI.
>>> COMING UP ON ABC 7 NEWS,
SOCIAL MEDIA SUMMIT WITHOUT TWO
BIG NAMES.
WHICH COMPANIES WILL BE MISSING
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE MEETING
THIS WEEK AND WHAT'S SET TO BE
DISCUSSED.
>>> NOT MUCH DOTTING THE RADAR.
WE DO HAVE A FLASH FLOOD WATCH.
TIME OUT SOME RAIN AND LOOK
AHEAD TO DRYER, MORE COMFORTABLE
DAYS IN OUR NEAR FUTURE.
THE NEWS AT
>> Announcer: YOU'RE WATCHING
ABC 7 NEWS AT 6:30 ON YOUR SIDE.
>> Anchor: NEW NUMBERS TONIGHT
ON THE PRESIDENT'S JOB
PERFORMANCE.
LATEST ABC NEWS WASHINGTON POST
POLL SHOWS THE PRESIDENT WITH
THE HIGHEST JOB APPROVAL RATING
IN THE PAST TWO AND A HALF
YEARS.
BUT NEARLY TWO-THIRDS OF THOSE
POLLED ALSO SAY THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAS NOT ACTED
PRESIDENTIAL.
RACHEL SCOTT WITH A BAB BREAKDOF
THE NUMBERS.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP SEEING THE
HIGHEST APPROVAL RATINGS OF HIS
PRESIDENCY IN THE LATEST ABC
NEWS WASHINGTON POST POLL.
44% OF AMERICANS APPROVE OF THE
JOB THE PRESIDENT IS DOING.
BUT STILL 53% DISAPPROVE.
AND AN EVEN GREATER NUMBER, 65%
OF THOSE POLLED SAY THE
PRESIDENT HAS ACTED
UNPRESIDENTIAL.
FORMER VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN
IS THE ONLY ONE WITH THE CLEAR
ADVANTAGE OVER THE PRESIDENT
AMONG REGISTERED VOTERS.
AHEAD BY TEN POINTS.
53% FOR BIDEN, 43% FOR THE
PRESIDENT.
>> HE'S THE BULLY THAT I KNEW MY
WHOLE LIFE.
HE'S THE BULLY THAT I HAVE
ALWAYS STOOD UP TO.
I THINK THE AMERICAN PEOPLE WANT
A PRESIDENT WHO HAS SOME
DIGNITY, WHO HAS A VALUE SET,
WHO IS ACTUALLY TRYING TO
RESTORE THE SOUL OF THIS
COUNTRY.
>> THE POLL ALSO TOUCHED ON
IMMIGRATION WITH 80% OF
AMERICANS SAYING IT WILL BE AN
IMPORTANT ISSUE IN THE 2020
VOTE.
JUST 40% APPROVE OF HOW THE
PRESIDENT IS HANDLING
IMMIGRATION.
REPORT LAST WEEK FROM THE
INSPECTOR GENERAL IS CALLING ON
THE DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND
SECURITY TO ADDRESS OVERCROWDING
AT DETENTION CENTERS.
>> THIS IS AN EXTRAORDINARY
CHALLENGES SITUATION.
WE HAD AN OVERFLOW SITUATION OF
HUNDREDS OF CHILDREN CROSSING
EVERY DAY.
THAT'S WHY WE WERE ASKING FOR
FUNDING FOR HEALTH AND HUMAN
SERVICES.
>> PICTURES IN THAT REPORT HAVE
MANY DEMOCRATS CALLING FOR
CHANGE AT THE SOUTHERN BORDER.
>> YOU MAKE SURE YOU ARE NOT
SEPARATING PARENTS FROM THEIR
KIDS, SOMETHING I WOULD DO IN MY
FIRST 100 DAYS AS PRESIDENT.
THEN YOU BRING IN COMPREHENSIVE
IMMIGRATION REFORM.
>> RACHEL SCOOT, ABC NEWS.
>>> SOCIAL MEDIA SUMMIT AT THE
WHITE HOUSE WILL NOT INCLUDE TWO
OF THE BIGGEST NAMES OF SOCIAL
MEDIA.
THEY SAY REPRESENTATIVE FROM
FACEBOOK AND TWITTER WERE NOT
INVITED.
THE SUMMIT IS SET TO ADDRESS
ISSUES FACING LARGE TECH
COMPANIES.
>>> TURNING TO WEATHER NOW, A
LITTLE BIT OF A COOLDOWN BUT,
BOY, IT IS STILL THICK.
>> Anchor: THAT'S THE THING, IT
FEELS PRETTY NICE.
JUST TAKE A COUPLE STEPS.
YOU WILL FEEL IT.
HUMIDITY STILL HIGH.
A LOT OF US DIDN'T GET TO 90
TODAY BUT IT FELT LIKE THE
90s.
TAKE A LOOK OUTSIDE, WE GO OVER
TO THE SHORE.
A LOT OF FOLKS PROBABLY HAD A
NICE FOUR-DAY WEEKEND AT THE
BEACH.
OCEAN CITY, RATHER DELIGHTFUL.
BLUE SKIES OUT THERE.
NICE BLUE WATER.
SAND LOOKING PRETTY PRISTINE.
79 DEGREES, EAST/NEARLY WINDS,
ALL IN ALL C CALM AND COMFORTABE
STRETCH.
FEW SHOWERS WEST, INTO WEST
VIRGINIA.
WESTERN MARYLAND.
FEW SHOWERS COMING DOWN TO THE
SOUTH.
ONE SHOWER UP IN SOUTHERN
MONTGOMERY COUNTY, RAIN ITSELF
OUT.
THIS CELL RIGHT HERE OVER
EASTERN OF ANNAPOLIS.
THE BAY BRIDGE.
WE WERE LOOKING AT THIS A LITTLE
WHILE AGO, NOW THE VISIBILITY
HAS COME BACK.
FOR A FEW MINUTES, THE RAIN WAS
COMING DOWN SO HARD YOU COULDN'T
SEE THE SPAN.
THAT IS THE EASTBOUND SPAN
THERE, WESTBOUND SPAN IS THE
ONES SLOWLY MOVING ACROSS THE
BAY ON THE OTHER SIDE.
MEANWHILE AT HOME, BUILDING DO
YOCUMULUS CLOUDS.
CHANTILLY THE SAME.
86 MARTINSBURG.
FACTOR IN THE HUMIDITY, MOST OF
US FEEL LIKE THE LOW 90s.
FEELING THE MUGGINESS AND
STICKINESS.
THE COMFORT SCALE, WE KNOW WHERE
WE ARE.
70s.
SOUPY.
THAT SOUPY AIR IS WITH US
TOMORROW.
SHOWERS, AIR WILL DRY OUT
THROUGH THE LATTER HALF OF THE
DAY.
TUESDAY AND WEDNESDAY, DRYER AIR
MOVES IN.
SO TUESDAY, WEDNESDAY REALLY
PROBAPROBABLY MY PICK OF THE WE.
THEY WILL BEGIN TO DEVELOP AND
THEY WILL ACTUALLY CARRY US INTO
THE FIRST HALF MANY TOMORROW
MORNING.
FOR THE MORNING DRIVE, I THINK
SOME SCATTERED RAIN AND MAYBE
THUNDER IS POSSIBLE IN THE
MORNING, DEFINITELY A LITTLE
SLOWER, YELLOW LIGHT, USE
CAUTIOUS.
THROUGH THE OVERNIGHT, PERIODS
OF RAIN.
YELLOWS AND ORANGES AND REDS,
MIDNIGHT TO MAYBE 1, 2 O'CLOCK
IN THE MORNING, EVEN AT
5 O'CLOCK FOR THE DRIVE, SOME
PERIODS OF RAIN WILL HAVE AN
EASTERLY WIND FLOW.
PROBABLY UP THROUGH LUNCHTIME.
BY LATE TOMORROW, SWIM MEETS
HAPPEN TOMORROW NIGHT, I THINK
WE WILL DRY OUT.
HUMIDITY WILL DROP BACK AND IT
DOES GET BETTER.
IT COULD BE A LOT OF RAIN.
SOME MODELS HINTING HALF INCH TO
TWO INCHES, AND THAT'S WHY WE
HAVE A FLASH FLOOD WATCH UP FOR
THE ENTIRE DNVMV.
YOUR FORECAST TOMORROW, SHOWERS,
RUMBLES OF THUNDER.
79, MUGGY.
AS WE GO THROUGH THE AFTERNOON,
WE WILL START TO DRY OUT.
TUESDAY, WEDNESDAY, PICK OF THE
WEEK.
THURSDAY MAYBE A FEW MORE
STORMS.
HUMIDITY AND TEMPERATURES ARE
NOT AS INTENSE FOR THE WEEK
AHEAD.
>> SO THE POOL DAY, BEACH DAY,
IF YOU ARE ABLE, TUESDAY,
WEDNESDAY, RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE WEEK.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHO HAS THOSE
DAYS OFF?
>> THANK YOU FOR ORDERING THAT.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
WE ARE ALL FOCUSED ON THE
WOMEN'S BASK SOCCER TEAM.
>> THE FRESH  FR PRESSURE WAS O.
RED WHITE AND BLUE SHINING
BRIGHT TONIGHT.
WHAT A PERFORMANCE BY THE U.S.
WOMEN'S NATIONAL SOCCER TEAM.
WORLD CHAMPS AGAIN.
YOU WILL HEAR FROM A HAPPY GROUP
OF LADIES NEXT IN SPORTS.
STAY WITH US.
>> NOW, THE TOYOTA SPORTS DESK
BROUGHT TO YOU BY YOUR LOCAL
TOYOTA DEALERS.
>> CAN WE ALL JUST SIT BACK AND
REFLECT FOR A MOMENT.
THIS U.S. WOMEN'S NATIONAL
SOCCER TEAM IS SPECIAL.
THE LADIES INSPIRING A NEW
GENERATION OF PLAYERS ON AND OFF
THE FIELD.
FROM START TO FINISH, COMPLETE
DOMINATION AT THE WOMEN'S WORLD
CUP.
THE AMERICANS WORLD CHAMPS
AGAIN.
THEY WERE TESTED IN THE FINAL.
NETHERLANDS CAME TO PLAY.
58 MINUTES, STILL SCORELESS.
ALEX MORGUE MORGAN GOES DOWN INE
BOX.
AWARDED A PENALTY.
RAPINOE DOES NOT DISAPPOINT.
TEN MINUTES LATER, OUR VERY OWN
ROSE LA VELLE, STAR FOR THE
WASHINGTON SPIRIT, LEFT-FOOTED
BEAUTY.
WHAT A TOURNAMENT SHE HAD.
OH, HOW SWEET IT IS.
LADIES, HOIST THAT TROPHY.
WHAT A MOMENT.
THE U.S. TOPPED THE NETHERLANDS
2 NIL WINNING THEIR SECOND
STRAIGHT WORLD CUP.
>> WE HAVE DONE EXACTLY WHAT WE
SET OUT TO DO.
WE HAVE DONE EXACTLY WHAT WE
WANT TO DO.
WE SAY WHAT WE FEEL.
ALL OF US REALLY.
I KNOW THAT MY VOICE SOMETIMES
IS LOUDER BUT IN THE
CONVERSATIONS, EVERYBODY IS IN
THIS TOGETHER.
WE ARE SUCH A PROUD AND STRONG
AND DEFIANT GROUP OF WOMEN.
I DON'T THINK WE HAVE REALLY
ANYTHING TO SAY.
>> I DON'T KNOW, I HAVEN'T BEEN
INVITED.
I CAN'T SAY.
>> I'M SURE YOU ARE ABOUT TO BE
INVITED.
>> I WOULDN'T BET ON THAT.
>> AND AFTER THE FINAL, THE
PARTY WAS ON.
RIGHTFULLY SO.
THE LADIES HAVING A GOOD OL'
TIME MAKING CONFETTI ANGELS ON
THE PITCH.
WILD SCENE IN THE LOCKER ROOM.
POPPING BOTTLES.
CHAMPAGNE WAS FLOWING.
NEW YORK CITY WILL BE THE PLACE
TO BE.
CHAMPIONSHIP TICKER TAPE PARADE.
>>> NUMBERS NEVER LIE, RIGHT
NOW, THE WASHINGTON NATIONALS
ARE PLAYING REALLY WELL.
SINCE MAY 24TH, THEY ARE 27-11
WITH A WIN TODAY OVER KANSAS
CITY, THE NATS WILL TIE THEIR
BEST 39-GAME MARK IN FRANCHISE
HISTORY.
THE NATS CLINGING TO AN ONE RUN
LEAD IN THE 7TH.
VICTOR ROBLIEY DOUBLES, HOME RUN
TO LEFT FIELD.
DOUBLES THE LEAD THERE.
2-0 TO WASHINGTON.
IT IS TIME TO DANCE.
HE HAS MOVES.
AT ELECTRICS GORDON SLAPS ONE
OFF THE WALL.
THAT BRINGS A RUN.
THIS GAME IS TIED AT 2.
THE NATS RESPOND.
ADAM EATON AT FIRST, ANTHONY
RANDONE KNOCKS THIS BASEBALL
INTO THE LEFT CENTER FIELD GAP.
EATONSLIDES IN SAFELY.
COUPLE BATTERS LATER, HO HOWIE
KENDRICK.
>>> AND THE NATS HAVE A
FOUR-DAYBREAK FOR THE ALL STAIR
GAME.
THEY ARE LOOKING GOOD HEADING
INTO THE SECOND HALF OF THE
SEASON OF THE WE'LLING RIGHT
>> Anchor: FOR TOMORROW, NOT
QUITE AS MILD.
ONLY AROUND 80 DEGREES, SHOWERS
AND STORMS IN THE MORNING.
LBY LATE TOMORROW MORNING, DRYER
AIR STICKING AROUND FOR MONDAY
AND TUESDAY.
>> THANK YOU FOR JOINING US, WE
WILL SEE RIGHT BACK HERE TONIGHT
AT 11.
Tonight on "America's
Funniest Home Videos"...
the season's final nine
winning families