>> I'M -- OH.
IT'S GENUINELY QUITE STRESSFUL.
THIS IS HILARIOUS.
I GOT AN OSCAR.
OKAY.
I HAVE TO THANK LOTS OF PEOPLE.
IF I FORGET ANYBODY, I'LL FIND
YOU LATER AND GIVE YOU A MASSIVE
SNOG, I'M SORRY I MIGHT FORGET
NOW.
MY BEST DIRECTOR, AND WITH EMILY
AND RACHEL, THE TWO LOVELIEST
WOMEN IN THE WORLD TO FALL IN
LOVE WITH AND TO DO TO WORK WITH
EVERY DAY.
YOU CAN IMAGINE, IT WASN'T A
HARDSHIP.
AND TO BE IN THIS CATEGORY WITH
THESE EXTRAORDINARY WOMEN.
GLENN CLOSE, YOU'VE BEEN MY IDOL
FOR SO LONG.
THIS IS NOT HOW I WANTED TO IT
TO BE, AND I THINK YOU'RE
AMAZING, AND I LOVE YOU VERY
MUCH.
I LOVE YOU ALL.
THANK YOU, LINDY KING, MY AGENT
WHO TOOK ME ON OVER 20 YEARS
AGO.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
AND OLIVE, HILDY, BRYNNA, MY MOM
AND DAD.
YOU KNOW.
AND MY KIDS, WHO ARE AT HOME AND
WATCHING.
IF YOU'RE NOT, THEN, WELL DONE.
BUT I SORT OF HOPE YOU ARE.
THIS IS NOT GOING TO HAPPEN
AGAIN.
AND ANY LITTLE GIRL WHO IS
PRACTICING THEIR SPEECH ON THE
TELLY, YOU NEVER KNOW.
AND I USED TO WORK AS A CLEANER,
AND I LOVED THAT JOB.
I DID SPEND QUITE A LOT OF TIME
IMAGINING THIS.
OH, PLEASE WRAP UP.
OKAY.
MY HUSBAND, ED.
MY BEST FRIEND, I LOVE YOU SO
MUCH.
25 YEARS, YOU'VE BEEN MY BEST
SUPPORTER.
HE'S GOING TO CRY.
I'M NOT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
FOX, EVERYBODY, THE CAST, THE
CREW, FRANCIES, SAM, THANK YOU O
MUCH.
LADY GAGA.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> COMING UP, THE ACADEMY AWARDS
FOR DIRECTING AND JULIA ROBERTS
PRESENTS BEST PICTURE.
WE'LL BE BACK IN A MOMENT.
♪♪
That's a cut.
(Bell rings)
Copy that.
We style the stars behind the
scenes in Walmart Fashion.
♪♪
We style the stars behind the
scenes in Walmart Fashion.
♪♪
(playing pool) - Wooo!
My man - All day! - Wooo!
♪♪
Wooo!
Hold my beer.
Actually...
♪♪
Budweiser Reserve Copper Lager.
There's a new Bud in Town.
Wooo!-Wooo! - Here we go
My son Forest, he was born
while my husband was deployed.
I video chatted
the entire birth.
I had great connectivity.
His entire platoon
was standing next to him.
They kept telling me, "You gotta
push! You gotta push!"
They all got to meet Forest,
all together.
About fifty of 'em.
And they all
started crying.
It was the sweetest thing
I have ever seen.
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now always includes
Apple Music on us.
Starting at only $40.
Only on Verizon.
[Man]
Seemed like you had a good time.
[Woman]
I had a really good time.
[Man]
I got a great shot of you.
[Woman]
Awww...
Aw look, there's Alejandro.
[Man]
Who's Alejandro?
[Woman]
Alejandro from work.
I told you about him.
[Woman]
He's so funny.
[WOMAN LAUGHS]
[Man]
That's better.
[Woman]
Hm?
[Man]
[Woman]
What?
[Man]
Nothing.
[MAN AND WOMAN LAUGHING]
♪
>>> PLEASE WELCOME LAST YEAR'S
WINNER OF THE ACADEMY AWARD FOR
DIRECTING, GUILLERMO DEL TORO.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> THANK YOU.
YESTERDAY, I HAD A FEVER, I WAS
VERY SICK.
BUT I WOULDN'T MISS THIS FOR THE
WORLD.
BECAUSE I FEEL A GREAT KINSHIP
WITH THIS AWARD, AND WITH THE
PEOPLE IT HONORS.
NO MATTER WHAT NAME IS IN THIS
ENVELOPE, AND I HAVE NOT PEEKED,
I WANT TO BE HERE AT THIS VERY
MOMENT.
BECAUSE EACH OF THE NOMINEES IN
THIS CATEGORY HAS MADE
PASSIONATE, PERSONAL FILMS, AND
EVERY ONE WILL LEAVE TONIGHT
WITH FILMS UNTOUCHED, THEY WILL
BE THE VERY SAME THEY WERE WHEN
THEY WALKED INTO THIS CEREMONY.
AND FOR THAT, YOU CAN BE VERY
PROUD.
[ APPLAUSE ]
HERE ARE THE NOMINEES FOR
ACHIEVEMENT IN DIRECTING.
SPIKE LEE, "BLACKKKLANSMAN."
PAWEL PAWLIKOWSKI, "COLD WAR."
YORGOS LANTHIMOS.
"THE FAVOURITE."
ALFONSO CUARON, "ROMA."
ADAM McKAY, "VICE."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO, THIS
NAME I CAN PRONOUNCE, ALFONSO
CUARON.
>> THIS IS THE FOURTH OSCAR FOR
ALFONSO CUARON.
HIS SECOND WIN TONIGHT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
BEING HERE DOESN'T GET OLD.
I WANT TO THANK SO MANY PEOPLE.
OBVIOUSLY, YALITZA APARICIO AND
MARINA, THEY WERE THE FILM, THEY
ARE TRULY THE FILM.
THE AMAZING CAST AND CREW.
GABRIELLA AND NICHOLAS, THE
PRODUCERS.
DAVID AND JONATHAN.
TED AND JULIA AT NETFLIX.
KELLY BUSH AND DAVID LERNER.
AND HENRY HOLMES.
NOW, I HAVE TO SAY, I HAD BETTER
TAKE OUT MY NOTES.
OH, YEAH, I WANT TO THANK THE
ACADEMY FOR RECOGNIZING THE FILM
CENTERED AROUND AN INDIGENOUS
WOMAN.
ONE OF THE MILLIONS OF THE
DOMESTIC WORKERS AROUND THE
WORLD WITHOUT RIGHTS, WHO HAVE
BEEN HISTORICALLY REGULALEGATED
THE BACKGROUND IN CINEMA.
THIS IS MUCH MORE IMPORTANT IN
TIMES WHEN WE'RE BEING
ENCOURAGED TO LOOK AWAY.
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> COMING UP NEXT, THE FINAL
AWARD OF THE EVENING, AS
JULIA ROBERTS PRESENTS THE
ACADEMY AWARD FOR BEST PICTURE.
STEVE: Is crispy
Applewood-smoked bacon
the best thing to ever happen
to the Big Mac or what?
SILA: No.
The Big Mac is clearly the best
thing to ever happen to bacon.
STEVE: Yeah, well bacon has
done just fine
without the Big Mac.
SILA: Without the Big Mac would
bacon even exist Steve?
STEVE: Yeah, yeah it would
exist.
STEVE: Oh, it's like that??!?!
McDonald's Classics with Bacon.
Only for a limited time.
Is it the best thing
to happen to our Classics?
Or to bacon?
Try for yourself and decide.
I am an emergency responder.
It takes me away from home,
uh... quite a bit.
Tenemos 4 niños.
Es muy importante siempre
estar conectados
para que él se sienta
parte de... del hogar.
Hacemos una video llamada
cuando se le cae
su primer diente.
Whether it's a text,
even just saying "I love you."
Siempre nos decimos
buenas noches.
I like the "buenas noches."
(chuckling)
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now always includes
Apple Music on us.
Starting at only $40.
Only on Verizon.
>>> LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, PLEASE
WELCOME ACADEMY AWARD WINNER,
JULIA ROBERTS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>>> OVER THE COURSE OF THE
EVENING, WE'VE SEEN HIGHLIGHTS
FROM EIGHT FILMS NOMINATED FOR
BEST PICTURE.
EACH IS UNIQUE IN THE STORY
BEING TOLD.
EACH IS DIFFERENT IN ITS APPEAL.
BUT THEY PROVE ONCE AGAIN THAT
REGARDLESS OF WHO YOU ARE OR
WHERE YOU LIVE, THESE ARE FILMS
THAT CONNECT US TO ONE ANOTHER.
ONCE AGAIN, HERE ARE THE
NOMINEES FOR BEST PICTURE.
>> "BLACK PANTHER."
"BLACKKKLANSMAN."
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY."
"THE FAVOURITE."
"GREEN BOOK."
"ROMA."
"A STAR IS BORN."
"VICE."
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> OH.
AND THE OSCAR GOES TO "GREEN
BOOK."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> "GREEN BOOK" HAS FIVE ACADEMY
AWARD NOMINATIONS THIS YEAR,
WINNING THREE OSCARS.
ACTOR IN A SUPPORTING ROLE,
ORIGINAL SCREENPLAY, AND BEST
PICTURE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> ALOHA.
AND THANK YOU TO THE MEMBERS OF
THE ACADEMY.
IT'S SUCH A PRIVILEGE.
THIS IS LIKE A DREAM.
WE NEED TO START BY THANKING OUR
FRIENDS AT PARTICIPANT MEDIA,
WHO HAVE BEEN WITH US ALL ALONG
THE WAY.
THANKS FOR THEIR BELIEF.
YEAH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WE CAN'T OVERLOOK UNIVERSAL AND
E1 AND LIONS GATE, AND I
PERSONALLY WANT TO THANK
CHRISTINA AND MATTY.
WE MADE THIS FILM WITH LOVE,
TENDERNESS, AND RESPECT.
AND IT WAS ALL DONE UNDER THE
DIRECTION OF PETE FARRELLY.
IT'S BEEN AN HONOR AND A
PRIVILEGE.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HE'S RIGHT, THIS IS, THE WHOLE
STORY IS ABOUT LOVE, IT'S ABOUT
LOVING EACH OTHER, DESPITE OUR
DIFFERENCES, AND FINDING OUT THE
TRUTH ABOUT WHO WE ARE, WE'RE
THE SAME PEOPLE.
THIS DOESN'T START, BY THE WAY,
WITHOUT VIGGO MORTENSEN.
RIGHT THERE, WE HAVE NO MOVIE,
ALL THESE AWARDS ARE BECAUSE
VIGGO AND MAHERSHALA AND LINDA,
BUT IT STARTED WITH VIGGO.
AND I GIVE YOU THIS, MY FRIEND.
I DIDN'T GET TO THANK A LOT OF
PEOPLE BEFORE.
I WANT TO THANK STEPHEN
SPIELBERG, OCTAVIA SPENCER,
CHRIS BOWERS, DONNA LANGLY,
ELLEN, BILL CURRY, THE FIRST
WRITER I EVER KNEW.
B
BETSY, TIM, CORDO WILFORD, AND
MY SISTER KATHY, SHE DIED A WEEK
BEFORE WE STARTED SHOOTING THIS,
BUT SHE NEVER LEFT MY SIDE.
>> THANKS VERY MUCH.
I WANT TO DEDICATE THIS TO --
OH, YOU CAN'T HEAR ME?
I WANT TO DEDICATE THIS TO OUR
GREAT FRIEND CARRIE FISHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> WELL, APPARENTLY, THAT WRAPS
UP THE 91st ACADEMY AWARDS.
CONGRATULATIONS TO ALL THE
NOMINEES AND WINNERS.
GOOD NIGHT TO MY CHILDREN.
AND THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
>> CONGRATULATIONS TO ALL OF
TONIGHT'S HONOREES FROM MARRIOTT
BONVOY.
30 HOTEL BRANDS.
ENDLESS EXPERIENCES.
REWARDS REIMAGINED.
EXPLORE THE PROGRAM AT
MARRIOTT.COM.
AIR TRANSPORTATION FOR THE
ACADEMY AWARDS PROVIDED BY DELTA
AIRLINES.
L.E.D. AND PROJECTION SERVICES
PROVIDED IN PART BY SENOVVA.
♪
,.
>> HISTORIC NIGHT AT THE OSCARS
WITH WOMEN WINNING BIG FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN HISTORY.
>> WE NEED THE MOST EFFECTIVE
TECHNOLOGY TO HELP US BE ABLE TO
SEE IN FRONT OF THOSE LARGE
VEHICLES.
>> WARNING OF BLIND SPOTS YOU
MIGHT NOT THINK OF.
>> DEADLY STORMS CAUSE PROBLEMS
FROM THE GULF COAST TO NIAGARA
FALLS.
ABC7 NEWS STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> NOW, ABC7 NEWS AT 11:00 ON
YOUR SIDE.
>> WE SAW IT HERE MOMENTS AGO,
"GREEN BOOK" WINNING BEFORE THE
PICTURE AT ACADEMY 88th ACADEMYD
WARDS AND THE STARS HEADING FOR
THE FANCY AFTER PARTIES.
WHAT DID YOU THINK ABOUT THE
ACADEMY AWARDS?
>> QUESTION ARE ON THE RED
CARPET.
SOME SURPRISES, SOME NOT SO
MUCH.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
GOOD EVENING.
BEHIND US, STARS ARE LEAVING AS
WE SPEAK RIGHT NOW AFTER A VERY
EXCITING NIGHT.
IT SEEMS LIKE EVERYONE CAME OUT
FOR WOOL'S BIGGEST NIGHT.
ANYONE WONDERING IN THE OSCARS
COULD SHOW IT OFF WITH NO HOST.
♪ WE WILL ROCK YOU ♪
>> LEARNED THEY COULD.
>> HUGE MUSICAL NUMBERS.
>> WELCOME TO THE ONE
MILLIONth ACADEMY AWARDS.
>> IF WE HOSTED IT WOULD GO LIKE
THIS.
>> WHAT KIND OF PLANS YOU GOT
LATER?
>> A GRAND ENTRY DURING THE SHOW
ON THE RED CARPET BEFORE.
>> HOPE EVERYBODY IS WATCHING AT
THE CAPITOL HILL.
>> AND SNEAKING IN A SPECIAL
GUEST.
>> SHE IS SMALL.
SHE FITS IN MY POCKET.
>> AND DANA AND MIKE TAKING THE
STAGE FOR "BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY"
--.
>> DANA SHARING WITH US THE
ORIGINAL PLAN FOR THE SCENE.
>> WE WERE TO GET OUT OF THE CAR
AND DO A BIG THING BUT THE
BUDGET WAS TOO...
WE WENT LIKE THAT, AND WE WERE
BUMPED BY THAT.
♪ IN THE SHALLOW ♪
>> MOST TALKED ABOUT WHEN
AMERICA WONDERED, WHAT IS GOING
TO HAPPEN NEXT?
>> BY THE WAY, WE WERE IN A
LARGE GROUP WATCHING THE MOMENT
AND EVERYONE GASPED, LADY GAGA
PICKING UP THE FIRST OSCAR AND
ANOTHER NIGHT FOR SPIKE LEE AND
AS WE TALKED ABOUT, HISTORIC
NIGHT FOR WOMEN PICKING UP 15
OSCARS ALTOGETHER.
NOW, WE WILL BREAK DOWN FOR YOU
JUST WHO WON THE MOST AWARDS
WHEN IT CAME TO MOVIES,
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY" TAKING HOME
FOUR OSCARS AND "GREEN BOOK"
WITH THREE OSCARS AND "ROMA"
WITH THREE AND "BLACK PANTHER"
WITH THREE.
NOW, YOU SPOKE ABOUT THE
PARTIES, AS WELL AND THAT IS
WHERE THE STARS ARE HEADING.
WE ARE NOT.
WE ARE HEADING TO BED.
WE WILL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
>> SPOILER ALERT.
>> THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING TO SAY
YOU ARE GOING TO A PARTY.
>> THANKS FOR THE GREAT WORK.
>> WE WILL SEE YOU SOON.
>> WE WILL HAVE THE RESULTS OF
THE POLL AND WHAT YOU THOUGHT OF
THE OSCARS WITHOUT A HOST, IT
MOVED ALONG.
WE HAVE THAT LATER.
>> MAYBE YOU WENT TOO OR HOST
ADD FANCY PARTY FOR THE OSCARS
BUT THIS LATE, METRO IS NOT AN
OPTION FOR YOU OR YOUR GUESTS TO
GET HOME.
WE ARE COVERING METRO WITH A
LOOK AT THE DEBATE OVER
RESTORING LATE NIGHT SERVICE
COMING UP FOR A VOTE ON
THURSDAY.
>> INCREASING METRO OPERATING
HOURS IS GETTING BIG SUPPORT
FROM RIDERS.
BUT IT IS NOT SO EASY AS JUST
KEEPING THE DOORS OPEN.
>> THE CHALLENGE IS BALANCING
SERVICE WITH MAINTENANCE.
IN 2016, THEY CUT HOURS TO ALLOW
TIME FOR MUCH NEEDED REPAIRS.
SINCE THAT TIME, ON FRIDAYS AND
SATURDAYS TRAINS STOP AT 1:00
A.M.
>> WE KNOW.
>> THEY USED TO RUN UNTIL 3:00.
>> WE GO OUT AND ENJOY AND HAVE
FUN.
>> BARTENDER SAID THE SHORTER
HOURS COST HIM.
>>  THE FACT I HAVE TO SPEND $50
OR $60 ON UBER OR LYFT IS
FRUSTRATING AND I DOING THAT SIX
DAYS OF THE WEEK SO...
IT ADDS UP.
>> THERE ARE FOUR SCHEDULED
OPTIONS WITH THE VOTE DAYS AWAY.
BACK TO THE 2016 HOURS.
SHIFT HOURS FOR A LATER MORNING
START.
EXTEND WEEKEND HOURS ONLY.
OR KEEP THEM THE WAY THEY ARE.
>> CONTINUE THE MAINTENANCE,
YES.
WE NEED TO BE SAFE.
>> SAFETY IS FIRST.
AT THE SAME TIME, WHEN THINGS
ARE DONE, THEY SHOULD HAVE IT
OPEN TO 3:00 A.M. IN THE
MORNING.
>>  THE DECISION COULD COME DOWN
TO DOLLARS.
THE FEDERAL TRANSIT
ADMINISTRATION IS THREATENING TO
DELAY FUNDING IF METRO
MAINTENANCE IS CAN CURTAILED.
>> THE BOARD WILL VOTE ON THE
HOURS CHANGE ON THURSDAY AT
10:00 A.M.
>> REMEMBER, YOU CAN DOWNLOAD
THE FREE ABC7 NEWSUP TO GET AN
UPDATE ON THAT VOTE AS SOON AS
IT HAPPENS ON THURSDAY.
>> WE HAVE BREAKING NEWS FROM
BOWIE WHERE SOMEONE WAS HIT AND
KILLED BY A TRAIN.
MARC TRAIN 694 STOPPED NEAR THE
STATION AND OTHER SERVICE ON THE
PENN LINE IS SUSPENDED.
POLICE ARE ONLY CONFIRMING A
PEDESTRIAN WAS HIT AND KILLED.
WE WILL GET YOU MORE INFORMATION
WHEN IT IS IN THE NEWSROOM.
>> FROM THE LIVE DESK WITH
REACTION AFTER POPE POP VOWED TO
CONFRONTS MEMBERS OF THE CLERGY
ACCUSED OF SEXUAL ABUSE WITH THE
WRATH OF GOD AFTER A SUMMIT IN
ROME GIVING BISHOPS THE POWER TO
TAKE ACTION ON ABUSE CASES.
OTHERS SAY IT IS NOT ENOUGH.
>> IT IS A FIRST STEP.
IT IS A NEEDED STEP.
AND NEEDED NOW.
>> IF HE CAN FIRE ANY BISHOP OR
CARDINAL THAT PROTECTS ABUSE AND
IT HELPS CHILDREN.
>> THOSE ABUSED BY PRIESTS
HANDED OUT LEAFLETS AT THE
BASILICA TODAY.
THEY ARE CALLING ON THE POPE D
TO DEMAND ALL RECORDS OF CHILD
SEXUAL ABUSE BE TURNED OVER TO
AUTHORITIES.
>> R. KELLY IS BEHIND BARS IN
CHICAGO AND HE WILL STAY PUT FOR
ANOTHER DAY OR TWO.
THE ATTORNEYS SAID THAT
ARRANGEMENTS ARE STILL MADE TO
PAY THE $100,000 NEEDED TO GET
HIM OUT ON BAIL.
HE TURNED HIMSELF IN ON FRIDAY
NIGHT AFTER BEING CHARGED WITH
TEN COUNTS OF CRIMINAL SEXUAL
ABUSE OVER 12 YEARS.
THAT INCLUDES AT LEAST THREE
UNDERAGE VICTIMS.
>> VIRGINIA'S LT. GOVERNOR WITH
A SURPRISE SPEECH TO THE STATE
SENATE AS THEY WRAPPED UP THE
LEGISLATIVE SESSION.
JUSTIN FAIRFAX RESISTED
WIDESPREAD CALLS TO RESIGN.
>> WE GO BACKWARD AND ALLOW IN A
RUSH FOR JUDGMENT FOR POLITICAL
LYNCHINGS WITHOUT ANY DUE
PROCESS, FACTS OR OFFED BEING
HEARD, WE DO A DISSERVICE TO
THIS BODY WHICH WE SERVE.
>> TWO WOMEN ACCUSE THE LT.
GOVERNOR OF SEXUAL ASSAULT.
FAIRFAX SAID HE WANTS A FULL
INVESTIGATION INTO THE
ALLEGATIONS AGAINST HIM AND IS
CONFIDENT IN THE TRUTH.
>> THE GENERAL ASSEMBLY ITSELF
WRAPPED UP AFTER PASSING A STATE
BUDGET THAT INCLUDES PAY RAISES
FOR TEACHERS AND STATE EMPLOYEES
AND SIGNIFICANT SPENDING ON
PUBLIC EDUCATION.
LAWMAKERS ALSO FROZE TUITION AT
SEVERAL IN-STATE INSTITUTIONS
AND PASSED A TAX OVERHAUL
MEANING REFUNDS FOR TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF FAMILIES.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS LOOKING
AHEAD TO INDEPENDENCE DAY,
TWEETING THIS MORNING THAT HE
PLANS TO HOST A PARTY FOURTH OF
JULY AT THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL IN
"SALUTE TO AMERICA," WITH FIRE
WORKS AND A SPEECH FROM THE
COMMANDER IN CHIEF.
WE WILL LET YOU KNOW MORE
DETAILS WHEN RELEASED.
>> NOW THE WEATHER.
HOPE YOU GOT OUTSIDE TODAY.
>> WHAT IS TO COME TOMORROW?
>> WE ARE TALKING WIND.
IT IS CALMER NOW THAN IT WAS.
BUT, STILL, 59-MILES-PER-HOUR
GUSTS IN CUMBERLAND AND 20 AND
30-MILES-PER-HOUR GUSTS AROUND
THE METRO REGION.
WE HAVE THE HIGH WIND WARNING
THAT REMAINS IN PLACE TO THE
NORTH.
THOSE WINDS ARE STILL 50-60.
WE HAVE ANOTHER WIND ADVISORY
TOMORROW AT 4:00 IN THE MORNING
AND EXPIRES AT 1:00 IN THE
AFTERNOON.
IT WILL BE MOST WINDY FROM 6:00
A.M. TO NOON IMPACTING THE
TEMPERATURES, AS WELL, TALKING
ABOUT THAT AND I WILL BREAK IT
DOWN IN A FEW MINUTES.
WINDY HERE TODAY.
THE GOOD NEWS?
NOTHING LEAK THE NASTY STORMS
THAT SWEPT THROUGH MISSISSIPPI
AND ALL THE WAY UP TO MICHIGAN
WITH THREE PEOPLE DEAD.
THERE WERE TORNADOES,
UNDERSTANDING AND BLIZZARD
CONDITIONS.
>> GOOD LORD, NO ONE WAS HURT OR
KILLED.
>> GEORGIA WAS HIT BY TORNADOES
THIS WEEKEND.
IN MISSISSIPPI CAMERAS ROLLING
AS THE LIGHTS WENT OUT AS
ANOTHER TWISTER SWIRLED
OVERHEAD.
>> FURTHER TO THE NORTH?
FLOODING IS THE STORY IN
TENNESSEE.
>> I WILL NOT LET IT GET TO
WHERE THEY HAVE TO TAKE ME OUT
IN A BOAT.
>> OTHERS WERE RESCUED BY BOATS.
THIS IS THE SCENE AT THE JACK
DANIELS DISTILLERY WITH RIVERS
OF WATER FLOWING WHERE THERE IS
GRASS.
>> IN 36 YEARS NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
>> UPSTATE NEW YORK THE WIND
CAUSING PROBLEMS IN BUFFALO
TEARING THE ROOF OF A BOOKSTORE
AND BROUGHT DOWN STREETLIGHTS
AND POWER POLES.
>>  THE WINDS ALSO A FACTOR IN
THE BLIZZARD CONDITIONS IN THE
MIDWEST.
MICHIGAN, HEAVY SNOW COLLAPSING
THE ROOF ON THIS BUS GARAGE.
NO ONE WAS HURT.
SEVERAL BUSES WERE CRUSHED.
IN NEBRASKA, NINE SEMI-TRUCKS
AND TWO CARS WERE INVOLVED IN A
NASTY CHAIN-REACTION CRASH IN
THE SNOW.