PLAN FOR D.C. FOURTH.
SHORT ON SPECIFICS.
SORTING THROUGH THE CONFUSION.
WILL D.C. EVEN PLAY ALONG?
A DOORBELL CAMERA SHOCKER.
A NERVOUS LOCKDOWN AN THEN A
SHOWDOWN!
♪ ♪
>> Announcer: NOW "ABC7 NEWS
AT 4:00".
ON YOUR SIDE.
>> RIGHT NOW AT 4:00, A
STORMWATCH7 WEATHER ALERT.
TREES ACROSS THE D.M.V. COMING
DOWN AND THIS ONE SLICING INTO
A FREDERICK HOME.
>> Nancy: THOUSANDS REMAIN
WITHOUT POWER ON THE DOLD AND
THE WINDY DAY.
THE BULK IN VIRGINIA.
ONE OF THE VISIBLE IMPACT
ASIDE FROM THE DOWN TREES ARE
THE WOBBLING PLANES AT THE
NATIONAL AIRPORT.
>> Alison: CAN YOU IMAGINE?
WHITE KNUCKLE MOMENTS FOR THE
PASSENGERS THERE.
ABC7 HAS TEAM COVERAGE.
THE NORTHERN VIRGINIA BUREAU
CHIEF TIM BARBER IS TRACKING
DAMAGE.
>> Nancy: CHIEF
METEOROLOGIST BILL KELLY WITH
THE FORECAST.
WE BEGIN WITH TIM AND WHAT HE
AS SEEN TODAY.
TIM?
>> Tim: WE ARE IN A
NEIGHBORHOOD THAT WAS WITHOUT
POWER TODAY.
THIS IS LIKE MANY
NEIGHBORHOODS THROUGHOUT
NORTHERN VIRGINIA AND MARYLAND
AS WELL.
THE POWER CREWS LEFT THE AREA
BECAUSE THEY WERE WORKING ON
THE POWER LINE.
YOU CAN SEE THAT TRAFFIC
LIGHTS ARE STILL OUT AS THEY
DANGLE IN THE WIND.
>> I WAS INSIDE FOR TEN
MINUTES.
I HEARD A LOUD BANG.
>> Tim: THAT WAS THE WIND
TOSSING THE TRANSFORMER TO THE
BACK OF THIS CAR.
WHILE BRUNO'S NEIGHBORS WERE
IN THE FRONT SEAT.
>> HAD FALLEN TO THE FRONT
AREA OF THE VEHICLE, WE
WOULDN'T BE HERE TODAY.
>> Tim: PEOPLE ACROSS THE
D.M.V. SPENT THE DAY DODGING
THE WIND'S DANGEROUS OBSTACLE
OBSTACLES.
TREES TOOK DOWN POWER LINES
AND BLOCKED STREETS IN D.C.,
MARYLAND AND VIRGINIA.
AIRLINE PASSENGERS ALSO HAD TO
RIDE OUT THE GUSTS THAT MADE
FOR SCARY CROSS WINDS.
>> IT'S QUITE BUMPY.
I CANNOT DESCRIBE TO LEVEL OF
THE BUMPINESS BUT IT WAS QUITE
BUMPY.
>> I THINK IT TOOK US 40
MINUTES TO ACTUALLY LAND.
IT WAS ONLY SUPPOSED TO TAKE
15 MINUTES.
>> SOME WERE DELAYED LANDING
BUT OTHERS DELAYED TAKING OFF.
>> ON THE WAY TO THE AIRPORT
THEY DELAYED THE FLIGHT 40
MINUTES.
>> Tim: AT ONE POINT 12,000
HOUSEHOLDS WERE WITHOUT POWER
IN NORTHERN VIRGINIA.
I JUST CHECK AND THE NUMBERS
HAVE GONE DOWN TO 2,700
CUSTOMERS.
REPORTING IN ARLINGTON.
WE WILL CHECK IN WITH BILL
WITH THE FORECAST.
>> Bill: THANK YOU, TIM.
SOME OF THE GUSTS, THE GOOD
NEWS IS THAT THINGS ARE
CALMING DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
LOOK AT THE PEAK GUSTS FROM
TODAY.
WE HAD 58-MILE-PER-HOUR GUST
IN LEESBURG.
TODAY IN D.C. WITH 44.
WE HAVE 54 IN HAGERSTOWN.
61 IN CUMBERLAND.
FREDERICK IS 49.
LET ME SHOW YOU THIS.
THIS IS A TREE TAKEN DOWN,
COMPLETELY UPROOTED, SLAMMING
INTO A HOME WHERE WE GOT WORD
THAT NOBODY WAS HURT FROM THE
VIDEO.
YOU CAN SEE IN A SECOND.
IT CUT THROUGH THE HOUSE LIKE
A BLADE.
SLICED IT UP.
IT WAS AMAZING TO SEE.
LET ME SHOW YOU THE GUSTS.
WE WILL GET YOU THE VIDEO.
THERE IT IS.
A TREE PUSHING IN THE HOUSE.
WE HAVE BEEN TOLD THAT HOUSE
IS GONE.
I MEAN PEOPLE AREN'T GOING TO
BE GOING IN THERE ANYTIME
SOON.
THAT'S GREAT NEWS.
IT'S SO SCARY WHEN YOU DEAL
WITH THESE, BUT NOBODY WAS
HURT.
I HAVE TREES NEAR MY HOUSE.
I GET CONCERNED WHEN THE WINDS
ARE AS HIGH AS THEY WERE.
THEY ARE CALMING DOWN.
IT'S STILL BREEZY.
37 IN D.C.
29 IN GAITHERSBURG.
THE WIND GUSTS IN FREDERICK IS
35.
39 IN CUMBERLAND.
DOWN FROM THE 61-MILE-PER-HOUR
GUSTS EARLIER.
ALSO, JUST WITHIN THE LAST
MINUTE OR TWO, A MAJORITY OF
THE WIND ADVISORIES HAVE
EXPIRED.
THERE IS STILL A LINGERING ALD
-- ADVISORY FOR UP NORTH
BUT THAT IS WINDING DOWN.
IT'S STILL A BREEZY NIGHT,
DON'T GET ME WRONG, BUT NOT TO
ADVISORY CATEGORY AND IT'S
CERTAINLY LESS THAN IT WAS.
TEMPERATURE WISE IN THE 40s.
FEELING COOLER WITH THE WIND
CHILL DROPPING TO 41 BY 8:00.
CHILLY NIGHT.
WE HAVE THAT AND MORE COMING
UP.
>> Nancy: THANKS, BILL.
NOT JUST WINDY HERE.
IN SYRACUSE, IT CREATED
WHITE-OUT CONDITIONS WITH SNOW
RESPONSIBLE FOR A PARTIAL
BUILDING COLLAPSE.
WHEN THE SUN CAME UP, IT WAS
APPARENT THERE WAS MORE DAMAGE
THAN FIRST THOUGHT.
YOU SEE IT THERE.
SCAFFOLDING FROM A BUILDING
UNDER CONSTRUCTION ALSO
KNOCKED DOWN OUT THERE.
DON'T BE CAUGHT OFF-GUARD WHEN
IT COMES TO THE WEATHER.
DOWNLOAD THE WEATHER APP.
IT'S FREE AND WE WILL SEND YOU
ALERTS BASED ON YOUR LOCATION.
>> Alison: A "7 ON YOUR
SIDE" UPDATE NOW.
THE STATE OF MARYLAND REPLACED
OR REPAIRED A DOZEN MAILBOXES
THAT WERE PLOWED THROUGH IN
LAST WEEK'S STORM.
ANGRY RESIDENT ALERTED ABC7 TO
THE PROBLEM AND SHOWED HOME
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO OF A PLOW
WIPING OUT HER MAILBOX.
WE POSTED THE VIDEO AND HOW TO
GET HELP ONLINE AT WJLA.com.
DEVELOPING TODAY, D.C. SCHOOL
EMPLOYEE CHARGED AFTER AN
INCIDENT AT DOROTHY HEIGHTS
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL INJURED A
SPECIAL NEED STUDENT.
TODAY NEW INFORMATION COMING
FROM THE POLICE AND COURT
DOCUMENTS.
STEPHEN TSCHIDA IS COVERING
D.C. WITH WHAT JUST HAPPENED
IN COURT.
STEPHEN?
>> Stephen: YEAH, ALISON,
MOMENTS AGO, THE DEFENDANT IN
THIS CASE, 33-YEAR-OLD WOMAN
WHO WORKED AS A TEACHER'S
AIDE, ALEXIS VAILED EXITED THE
COURTHOUSE.
WE GOT VIDEO OF HER AS SHE WAS
LEAVING.
YOU CAN SEE SHE IS THE SMALLER
WOMAN ON THE SIDE, CLOSEST TO
THE CAMERA.
NOW SHE IS CHARGED WITH
WORKING AT DOROTHY HEIGHT
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL ON FEBRUARY
1.
THAT IS WHEN SHE IS ALLEGED TO
HAVE BEEN WORKING WITH A
7-YEAR-OLD BOY WITH DOWN
SYNDROME.
WITNESSES SAY THE BOY LIKED TO
BOUNCE ON A VERY LARGE YOGA
BALL.
THAT DAY HE WAS ON HIS STOMACH
BOUNCING ON THE BALL AND VAILS
APPROACHED HIM, KICKED THE
BALL OUT FROM UNDERNEATH HIM,
CAUSING THE CHILD TO PLUNGE TO
THE FLOOR WITH SUCH FORCE, HE
SPLIT HIS CHIN OPEN.
HE WAS RUSHED TO THE HOSPITAL,
UNDERWENT SURGERY TO CLOSE THE
WOUND.
ACCORDING TO COURT DOCUMENTS.
VAIL TOLD INVESTIGATORS THAT
SHE DID KICK THE BALL BUT SHE
WAS UNAWARE THAT THE CHILD
INJURED HIMSELF BECAUSE SHE
TURNED AWAY QUICKLY.
NOW THE HEARING EXAMINER DID
RELEASE HER ON HER OWN
RECOGNIZANCE PENDING THE COURT
APPEARANCE BUT ORDERED HER TO
STAY AWAY FROM THE 7-YEAR-OLD
BOY WITH DOWN SYNDROME AND
REFRAIN FROM ANY WORK WITH
CHILDREN.
REPORTING LIVE, STEPHEN
TSCHIDA, ABC7 NEWS.
>> Alison: THANK YOU.
THE SUPREME COURT WILL HEAR
ARGUMENTS WEDNESDAY FOR AND
AGAINST MOVING THIS.
THIS IS WHAT IS CALLED "THE
PEACE CROSS."
A 40-FOOT CROSS ON STATE LAND
AT THE JUNCTION OF BLADENSBURG
ROAD, BALTIMORE AVENUE AND
ANNAPOLIS ROAD IN PRINCE
GEORGE'S COUNTY.
SOME ARGUE THE 93-YEAR-OLD
CROSS VIOLATES THE SEPARATION
OF CHURCH AND STATE.
SUPPORTERS DISAGREE SAYING IT
HAS A SECULAR PURPOSE,
HONORING 49 LOCAL RESIDENTS
WHO DIED DURING WORLD WAR I.
>> Nancy: NOW TO THE CHAOS
IN THE COMMONWEALTH.
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR JUSTIN
FAIRFAX SPEAKING OUT ON SUNDAY
IN A FORUM WHERE NOBODY COULD
ASK QUESTIONS.
THIS AS TWO WOMEN ARE ACCUSING
FAIRFAX OF SEXUAL ASSAULT.
RICHARD REEVE WITH FAIRFAX'S
CLOSING COMMENT IN RICHMOND.
RICHARDS FAR FROM THE POWERS
OF RICHMOND.
>> THERE IS AN INVESTIGATION.
>> Richard: MANY HERE
THINKING ABOUT LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR JUSTIN FAIRFAX AND
HIS SUNDAY SPEECH.
>> WE ALLOW FOR POLITICAL
LUNCHINGS WITHOUT ANY DUE
PRO -- LYNCHINGS WITHOUT ANY
EVIDENCE OR FACTS, WE DO A
DISSERVICE TO THE BODY WE
SERVE.
>> Richard: HE IS ADDUCED OF
TWO WOMEN OF SEXUAL ASSAULT.
REPUBLICAN LAWMAKERS INVITED
VANESSA TYSON AND MEREDITH
WATSON TO TESTIFY PUBLICLY.
>> THEY SHOULD BE ABLE TO
SPEAK.
ABSOLUTELY.
IT'S A LITTLE WORRISOME.
HE SHOULD BE SAYING LET THEM
SPEAK.
RICHARDS IN HIS SPEECH,
FAIRFAX COMPARED HIMSELF TO
VICTIMS OF LYNCHINGS OF PEOPLE
OF COLOR IN JIM CROW ERA.
>> I HEARD MUCH ABOUT
ANTILYNCHING ON THE FLOOR OF
THIS VERY SENATE WHERE PEOPLE
WERE NOT GIVEN ANY DUE PROCESS
WHATSOEVER.
>> Richard: AFTER THE
SPEECH, DEAD SILENCE.
G.W. POLITICAL EXPERT SAY SOME
MIGHT FEEL THE COMPARISON IS
WRONG.
>> HERE YOU HAVE TWO SEEMINGLY
CREDIBLE AFRICAN-AMERICAN
WOMEN WHO HAVE MADE A CHARGE
AGAINST MR. FAIRFAX, WHO IS A
PERSON IN A POSITION OF
CONSIDERABLE INFLUENCE.
>> Richard: STILL, FAIRFAX
HAS STRONG SUPPORTERS.
>> IT SOUNDS ACCURATE.
WHERE WERE THE ACCUSATIONS
WHEN HE WAS RUNNING FOR THE
OFFICE?
>> Richard: RIGHT NOW NO
CLEAR ENDING TO THE POLITICAL
DRAWMA.
IN FALLS CHURCH, RICHARD
REEVE, ABC7 NEWS.
>> Alison: PRESIDENT TRUMP
DEPARTING FOR VIETNAM THIS
AFTERNOON, PREPARING FOR HIS
SECOND MEETING WITH NORTH
KOREA'S KIM JONG UN.
THE STAKES HIGHER AFTER HIS
FIRST FACE TO FACE OPENED
DIALOGUE BUT PRODUCED LITTLE
SPECIFICS TO A RESOLUTION.
ABC7'S ELIZABETH HUR WITH
TRUMP TAMPING DOWN
EXPECTATIONS.
>> Reporter: DEPARTING
WASHINGTON FOR VIETNAM,
PRESIDENT TRUMP SOUNDING OPT
MYSTIC.
>> President Trump: I THINK
WE WILL HAVE A TREMENDOUS
SUMMIT.
>> Reporter: SPEAKING TO THE
NATION'S GOVERNORS AHEAD OF
THE SUMMIT WITH NORTH KOREAN
LEADER KIM JONG UN FOR THE
SECOND TIME IN LESS THAN A
YEAR.
>> President Trump: WE ARE
SPEAKING AND WE ARE SPEAKING
LOUD.
I THINK WE CAN HAVE A VERY
GOOD SUMMIT.
>> Reporter: KIM ALREADY ON
HIS WAY, SEEN HERE ON SATURDAY
BOARDING A TRAIN.
NOT A PLANE.
REPORTEDLY TO HAVE BETTER
CONTROL OVER SECURITY.
AND AIRTIGHT SECURITY IS WHAT
OFFICIALS IN HANOI ARE
PROMISING, SPENDING A WEEK
PREPARING FOR THE HISTORIC
SUMMIT.
THE FOCUS THIS TIME AROUND IS
ON NORTH KOREA GIVING UP ITS
NORTH KOREAS.
THAT, ACCORDING TO THE
U.S. INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS,
IS UNLIKELY.
>> ITS LEADERS ULTIMATELY VIEW
NUCLEAR WEAPONS AS CRITICAL TO
REGIME SURVIVAL.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT
ALSO STRUCK A MORE REALISTIC
TONE OVER THE WEEKEND,
TWEETING THAT THE TWO LEADERS
EXPECT A CONTINUE --
CONTINUATION OF PROGRESS AND
ADDING THE WORD
"DENUCLEARIZATION?"
AND FOLLOWED THIS UP ON
MONDAY.
>> President Trump: WE WANT
DENUCLEARIZATION.
I THINK HE WILL HAVE A COUNTRY
THAT WILL SET RECORD FOR SPEED
IN TERMS OF AN ECONOMY.
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS
REMAIN SKEPTICAL, CALLING FOR
A CONCRETE PLAN.
THEY SAY THIS SUMMIT MANES
NOTHING UNLESS THEY COME ONE A
PLAN FOR FULL
DENUCLEARIZATION.
REPORTING FROM NORTHWEST, I'M
ELIZABETH HUR, ABC NEWS.
>> Nancy: DEVELOPING THIS
AFTERNOON, R. KELLY ATTORNEYS
SPEAK FOR HIM IN COURT AND
ENTER NOT GUILTY PLEA ON
BEHALF OF THE SINGER WHO IS
FACING TEN SEX CRIME CHARGES.
THIS AS MICHAEL AVENATTI
REPRESENTING TWO OF THE
ALLEGED VICTIMS GIVE POLICE
TAPES THAT HE SAYS ARE
EVIDENCE.
HE SAYS HE HAS MORE WHERE THAT
CAME FROM.
>> WE HAVE COME TO LEARN OF
THE EXISTENCE OF YET A THIRD
VIDEOTAPE.
I BELIEVE THERE ARE MANY, MANY
VIDEOTAPES, I MIGHT ADD.
BUT A THIRD VIDEOTAPE THAT
DEPICTS ADDITIONAL SEXUAL
ASSAULT, AND ABUSE BY R.
KELLY.
>> Nancy: KELLY, WHO IS
HAVING TROUBLE FINDING THE
$100,000 TO POST BOND REMAINS
BEHIND BARS.
>>> PATRIOTS OWNER ROBERT
KRAFT OFFICIALLY CHARGED WITH
SOLICITING A PROSTITUTE.
THE 77-YEAR-OLD BILLIONAIRE IS
ACCUSED OF VISITING A DAY SPA
IN JUPITER, FLORIDA, THAT WAS
ALLEGEDLY BEING USED FOR
PROSTITUTION.
25 OTHER PEOPLE ALSO CHARGED
HERE.
COURT DOCUMENTS SAY KRAFT
VISITED THE SPA THE SAME DAY
THAT THE PATRIOTS PLAYED IN
AND WON THE A.F.C.
CHAMPIONSHIP.
STILL AHEAD AT 4:00 --
>> ♪ I ALE -- I'LL NEVER LET
YOU GO ♪
>> Nancy: SWIFT HELPS A
COUPLE CELEBRATE THEIR
ENGAGEMENT AND HOW SHE HELPED
PULL OFF THE SURPRISE OF A
LIFETIME.
>> Alison: PLUS --
>> HOLD ON.
>> Alison: A FIRST-PERSON
VIEW FROM AN OFFICER'S BODY
CAMERA AS HE RISSICS HIS --
RISKS HIS OWN LIFE TO SAVE A
DOG STRANDED IN A FRIGID POND.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP WANTS TO
HOLD A NEW EVENT AT THE
LINCOLN MEMORIAL THAT WOULD
TAKE PLACE ON JULY 4th.
HOW WOULD THAT AFFECT THE
OTHER TRADITIONS THAT ALREADY
TAKE PLACE ON INDEPENDENCE
DAY?
I'M TOM ROUSSEY.
I WILL HAVE A LOOK AT THAT
COMING UP.
>> Nancy: THAT IS OUR
INSTAPOLL.
IF PRESIDENT TRUMP HOSTS HIS
OWN PARTY ON THE MALL, WOULD
YOU GO?
>> Alison: HEAD TO
WJLA.com/VoteNow TO
PARTICIPATE.
THE NUMBERS WILL SHOW UP LIVE
AS YOU WEIGH IN ONLINE AND
TYou still stressed about buying
AS Your first house, sweetie?
AFTER THE
Yeah,
I thought doing some hibachi
grilling would help take
my mind off it all.
Maybe you could relieve
some stress by calling GEICO
for help with our
homeowners insurance.
GEICO helps with
homeowners insurance?
They sure do.
And they could save us
a bundle of money too.
I'm calling GEICO
right now.
Cell phone?
It's ringing.
Get to know GEICO and
see how much you could
save on homeowners and
condo insurance.
>> Alison: DID YOU SEE THIS,
THIS WEEKEND?
PRESIDENT TRUMP TWEETING THAT
EVERYONE SHOULD SAVE THE DATE.
HE IS HOSTING A BIG FOURTH OF
JULY CELEBRATION AT THE
LINCOLN MEMORIAL.
>> Nancy: FIREWORKS
INCLUDED.
THAT IS PART OF THE ANNUAL
TRADITION, AS WELL.
WHAT IS NOT CLEAR, WOULD THIS
BE CELEBRATE FROM THE PARTY
HIGHER UP ON THE MALL?
THE QUESTION TODAY, WOULD YOU
GO TO THE PRESIDENT'S PARTY?
GO TO WJLA.com/VoteNow TO
LET US KNOW.
THE NUMBERS ARE SHOWING UP
LIVE ON TELEVISION.
>> Alison: AS YOU VOTE, OUR
TOM ROUSSEY NOW WITH EARLY
REACTION TO THIS.
HI, TOM.
>> Tom: WE ARE HEARING A LOT
OF OPINIONS.
BUT A LOT OF QUESTIONS, TOO.
A CAPITOL FOURTH IS A CONCERT
THAT PBS AIRS AND I TAKES ON
THE WEST LAWN BEFORE THE
FIREWORKS.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS HE WANTS TO
PUT HIS EVENT ON THE OTHER END
OF THE NATIONAL MALL AT THE
LINCOLN MEMORIAL.
SO THERE ARE QUESTIONS HOW
WOULD ONE EVENT POTENTIALLY
AFFECT THE OTHER?
JULY 4th IS D.C.S BIGGEST
DAY OF THE YEAR, FILLED WITH
TRADITIONS INCLUDING THE
FIREWORKS, A PARADE, AND A
CONCERT CALLED "A CAPITOL
FOURTH" AIRED BY PBS.
ONE THING THAT IS NOT A
TRADITION ON JULY FOURTH, A
PRESIDENT SPEAKING.
BUT PRESIDENT TRUMP MAY WANT
TO CHANGE THAT.
OVER THE WEEKEND HE TWEETED,
"HOLD THE DATE.
WE WILL BE HAVING ONE OF THE
BIGGEST GATHERINGS IN THE
HISTORY OF WASHINGTON, D.C. ON
JULY FOURTH.
IT WILL BE CALLED 'A SALUTE TO
AMERICA' AND WILL BE HELD AT
THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL."
HE GOES ON TO SAY THERE WOULD
BE FIREWORKS AND HE WOULD
SPEAK.
SOME WE TALKED TO WOULD GO.
>> SURE.
I'LL BE HERE.
>> Tom: BUT REACTION IS
MIXED.
>> I DON'T SEE THE NEED FOR
IT.
IT DOESN'T NEED TO BE MADE
MORE POLITICAL.
THAT IS MY REASONING.
>> Tom: ONE THING THAT IS
UNCLEAR WOULD IT REPLACE OR
HAPPEN IN ADDITION TO CAPITOL
FOURTH?
THE WHITE HOUSE SAID IT HAD
NOTHING TO ADD TO THE
PRESIDENT'S TWEET OTHER THAN
HE IS EXCITED ABOUT THE EVENT.
THE NATIONAL PARK SERVICE SAID
NO FINAL DECISIONS HAVE BEEN
MADE WE CONTINUE TO WORK ON
CREATING SALUTE TO AMERICA
PROGRAM TO BRING AMERICANS
FROM ALL OVER THE COUNTRY
TOGETHER IN CELEBRATION OF OUR
GREAT NATION.
PARK SERVICE SPOKESPERSON SAID
AS FAR AS HE KNEW A CAPITOL
FOURTH IS STILL SCHEDULED TO
HAPPEN ON THE WEST LAWN OF THE
CAPITOL LIKABLE.
PBS WOULDN'T EVEN COMMENT TO
US BUT THE WEBSITE SAYS THAT
IT TAKE PLACE JULY 4th
THERE SO IT APPEARS LIKE WHAT
THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO DO
WOULD BE SEPARATE FROM THAT.
REPORTING LIVE ALONG THE
NATIONAL MALL ON A WINDY DAY,
I'M TOM ROUSSEY, ABC7 NEWS.
>> Alison: IT WILL BE WARMER
JULY 4th.
WE KNOW THAT MUCH.
ALL RIGHT, TOM.
THANK YOU.
WELL, ONE COUPLE, TWO BIG FANS
OF TAYLOR SWIFT.
WHEN ALEX GOLDSCHMIDT READY TO
PROPOSE TO HIS BOYFRIEND HE
FIGURED HE WOULD E-MAIL THE
STAR AND TELLING HER HOW MUCH
THE SONG "KING OF MY HEART"
MEANT TO THEM AND ASKED IF SHE
WOULD HELP CELEBRATE THE
ENGAGEMENT.
HER APPEARANCE WAS A SURPRISE.
SHE BROUGHT THE GUITAR TO PLAY
THE COUPLE'S SPECIAL SONG.
>> ♪ I'LL NEVER LET YOU GO ♪
♪ KING OF MY HEART ♪
♪ BODY AND SOUL ♪
♪ AND ALL AT ONCE ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> WOW!
HOW COOL IS THAT?
THE COUPLE SAID THEY COULDN'T
THANK HER ENOUGH.
I'M PRETTY SURE SHE WILL GET
AN INVITE TO THE WEDDING.
>> I WOULD SAY, I CAN'T
BELIEVE SHE WENT.
THAT IS SO COOL.
>> Alison: ISN'T THAT
WONDERFUL?
>> Nancy: YEAH.
>> Alison: EXCITING.
>> Nancy: DO YOU REMEMBER
LAST YEAR WHEN THERE WAS THE
$1.5 BILLION MEGA MILLIONS
JACKPOT?
SOMEONE IN SOUTH CAROLINA WAS
THE ONLY PERSON TO HIT IT.
NO ONE HAS COME FORWARD.
THE APRIL 19 DEADLINE IS
LOOMING.
SOMETHING ELSE THAT IS KEY,
THE STORE WOULD MISS OUT ON
THE BONUS AND THEY COULD NOT
OFFER REBATES TO EVERY CITIZEN
WHICH THEY PLAN FOR ON THE
POTENTIAL COLLECTION.
TIME IS LOOMING.
MUST SEE VIDEO.
>> HOLD ON.
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW.
>> Nancy: LOOK AT THAT.
OFFICER'S BODY CAMERA SHOWS
POLICE SERGEANT IN UPSTATE NEW
YORK.
THIS IS A DOG.
HE IS RESCUING THE DOG.
IT FELL THROUGH THE ICE IN
ERIE CANAL.
THE DOG IS OKAY BUT THEY HAVE
POSTED THIS TO SOCIAL MEDIA
HOPING TO REUNITE THE POOR GUY
WITH THE OWNER.
>> WOW!
>> Nancy: TERRIFYING.
>> Alison: YEAH.
WE WANT TO SHOW YOU THE
PICTURE BEHIND US TO GIVE YOU
AN IDEA.
IT'S STILL WINDY OUT THERE.
>> Nancy: BEAUTIFUL SHOT.
NATIONAL HARBOR.
GORGEOUS.
WE ARE BELOW ADVISORY
CRITERIA.
>> Bill: THE WINDS ARE STILL
GUSTING TO 35, 38 MILES PER
HOUR.
THAT IS DOWN FROM WHERE WE
WERE EARLIER, WHICH IS, OF
COURSE, GREAT NEWS.
OUT IN LOUDOUN COUNTY.
YOU IN LEESBURG HAD GUST OF 58
MILES PER HOUR EARLIER ON
TODAY.
IT'S CURRENTLY 50 DEGREES IN
D.C. AS WE LOOK HERE LIVE FROM
THE MANDRIN ORIENTAL CAMERA.
WE HAVE 47 IN CHANTILLY.
MARTINSBURG IS 43.
WARMER IN LEONARDTOWN.
THE WINDS SUSTAINED GENERALLY
BETWEEN 15 TO 25 MILES PER
HOUR.
SOME LESS THAN THAT.
GUSTS UP TO 37.
31 FOR YOU IN WINCHESTER
AROUND LEONARDTOWN.
28 IN CUMBERLAND.
PUSHING 40 MILES PER HOUR.
SO DEFINITELY A WINDY EVENING.
NO DOUBT ABOUT THAT.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
IF YOU NOTICE TODAY, YOU WENT
OUT AND THE WINDS, THINGS ARE
CHURNED UP.
BEAUTIFUL SKY.
NICE AND CLEAN.
THE AREA OF THE LOW PRESSURE
RESPONSIBLE MOVING AWAY FROM
THE REGION.
THEREFORE, THE WINDS WILL
SLACKEN UP AS WE GO INTO THE
EVENING HOURS TONIGHT.
THERE ARE FEW IF ANY CLOUDS
OVER THE ENTIRE STATE OF WEST
VIRGINIA, VIRGINIA, MARYLAND,
DELAWARE.
NORTH CAROLINA.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL OUTSIDE.
WE ARE AT 50 DEGREES.
IT'S WINDY SO IT DOESN'T FEEL
THAT GREAT.
WE HAVE 39 IN ELKIN AND 33 IN
PITTSBURGH.
VIRGINIA BEACH AT 56 DEGREES.
SO WE ARE DRY FOR THIS
EVENING.
THE TEMPERATURES WILL DROP ON
DOWN.
I WANT TO FOCUS IN ON THE NEXT
WEATHER MAKER TO POTENTIALLY
BRING US SNOW FOR FRIDAY
MORNING.
WE ARE FOCUSED IN ON IT.
I'M RUNNING THIS BECAUSE THIS
WILL SHOW US TWO MODELS THAT
WE LOOK AT.
WE ARE MANY DAYS AWAY.
BUT THE BLUE ON THIS MONEY,
THE EUROPEAN MODEL SHOWS SNOW
BY FRIDAY.
GREEN ON THE AMERICAN MODEL IS
RAIN.
EVEN IF THIS ONE VERIFIES, IT
WOULDN'T BE MUCH.
WATCH AS WE GO TO THE
MID-TO-THE LATE MORNING.
IT'S GONE.
THE BLUE POTENTIAL, THE
AMERICAN KICKS OUT OF HERE.
BY THE END OF THE DAY ON
FRIDAY, I WOULDN'T "MUCH IN
THE WAY OF RAIN.
THAT IS THE NEXT WEATHER MAKER
TO KEEP AN EYE ON.
DRY TONIGHT.
IT'S CHILLY.
DRY TOMORROW.
FEW ADDED CLOUDS.
50 DEGREES.
NOT AS WINDY.
NOT A BAD DAY TOMORROW.
THERE WILL BE SUNSHINE IN THE
MORNING.
FEW CLOUDS IN THE AFTERNOON.
SAME WITH WEDNESDAY.
THE NEXT FOCUS IS FRIDAY.
IN THE MORNING.
BEFORE THAT TRANSITION OUT OF
HERE.
LINGERS TO SATURDAY.
THERE YOU GO.
BREEZY.
HANG ON TO YOUR HAT IF YOU ARE
HEADING OUT TONIGHT.
>> Nancy: THANK YOU.
NEXT FOR US ON "ABC7 NEWS AT
4:00" --
>> I DON'T BELIEVE THAT
AMERICA BELIEVES THAT YOU
COULDN'T GET A TICKET TO THE
OSCARS.
>> Nancy: THE DAY AFTER KIDD
O'SHEA TALKS OSCARS WITH KELLY
AND RYAN.
YOU DO NOT WANT TO MISS THEIR
TAKE.
>> Alison: AT 4:30, A "7 ON
YOUR SIDE" CONSUMER ALERT.
THE S.U.V. OR TRUCK YOU THINK
IS SAFE FOR YOUR FAMILY HAS A
BIG HIDDEN DANGER.
JUST HOW LONG BLIND SPOTS ARE
AND WHAT IS DONE TO MAKE THE
VE
I know what it means to
have reliable support.
I found a company
who believes in me.
They look out for me.
And they help me grow my career.
At Comcast it's my job to
constantly monitor our network,
prevent problems, and to help
provide the most reliable
service possible.
My name is Tanya,
I work at the network
operations center for Comcast.
We're working to make things
simple, easy and awesome.
>> Alison: SO OUR KIDD
O'SHEA DID A WONDERFUL JOB,
OUT IN L.A. COVERING THE
OSCARS ON ABC7 THIS WEEKEND.
THIS MORNING HE COMPLETED HIS
HOLLYWOOD TRIP TO ATTEND "LIVE
WITH KELLY AND RYAN AFTER
OSCAR SHOW."
>> Nancy: HOW COOL IS THAT?
THIS IS WHAT THEY REVEALED TO
KIDD ABOUT THE OSCAR NIGHT
EXPERIENCE.
>> Kidd: I DON'T BELIEVE
AMERICA BELIEVES YOU COULDN'T
GET A TICKET TO AS -- TO THE
OSCARS.
>> THEY SHOULD BELIEVE IT.
I WAS HEADED THERE ONE MINUTE
AFTER THE HOUR.
I POSTED ENCHILADAS.
>> YOU CAN'T CALL SOMEONE TO
SAY I NEED A TICKET?
>> KELLY WAS BUSY.
>> I DIDN'T HAVE A TICKET
EITHER.
I WAS ON THE STAGE BUT IF I
TRIED TO WALK IN THE AUDIENCE
THERE WOULD HAVE BEEN A
DIFFERENT STORY.
>> WE'D BE IN OSCAR JAIL.
AND THEY HAVE ONE.
>> WHAT A BEAUTIFUL INTERVIEW.
>> IT WAS AN INCREDIBLE
MOMENT.
THERE WERE SO MANY -- I MANE
WE COULD HAVE DONE A ONE-HOUR
INTERVIEW.
HE WAS SO REVEALING AND
VULNERABLE BACKSTAGE.
AALWAYS SAY PEOPLE WHO JUST
WON AN ACKED -- ACADEMY AWARD
WILL TELL YOU ANYTHING.
BUT HE IS PRIVATE.
SO TO GET MOMENTS ABOUT THE
UPBRINGING AND FAMILY WERE
SPECIAL AND MEANINGFUL.
>> Alison: ALL RIGHT.
THANKS, KIDD.
COMING UP AT "ABC7 NEWS AT
4:00" --
>> I COULDN'T BELIEVE, I
COULDN'T SEE NINE KIDS.
>> Alison: THE BLIND SPOTS
ON VEHICLES INTENDED FOR
FAMILIES SHOCKINGLY LARGE.
THE STORY YOU NEED TO SEE AND
WHAT IS BEING DONE TO MAKE
VEHICLES SAFER.
>> Nancy: PLUS, ABOUT A YEAR
AFTER A D.C. ARTIST WAS
MURDERED THE TRIAL BEGINS.
AFTER WE SAW THE VIDEO IN THE
SEARCH FOR A POTENTIAL KILLER,
THE NEW EVIDENCE PROSECUTORS
ARE NOW SHARING IN COURT.
THAT IS NEXT.
>> Alison: AHEAD AT "ABC7
NEWS AT 5:00" --
SAVED FROM THE FLAMES.
FIREFIGHTERS SAVE PUPPIES FROM
A BURNING HOME IN THE
DISTRICT.
5:00, SIDE WITH A COMMON
MISTAKE THAT COSTS A FAMILY
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance
so you only pay
for what you need.
Great news for anyone wh-
Uh uh - I'm the one who
delivers the
news around here.
♪  ♪
Liberty Mutual
has just announced
that they can customize
your car insurance
so that you only
pay for what you need.
This is Phoebe
Buckley, on location.
Uh... thanks, Phoebe.
♪  ♪
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
Z3458Z ZI0Z
Y3458Y YI0Y
Your favorite restaurants now
deliver with DoorDash.
♪
It doesn't matter
where you are.
♪
It doesn't matter what
you're hungry for.
It doesn't even matter
how many you are.
♪
Restaurants come to you.
Delicious at your door.
Download DoorDash.
First order, no delivery fee.
>> Announcer: YOU'RE
WATCHING "ABC7 NEWS AT 4:00".
ON YOUR SIDE.
>> Michelle: AN ARTIST
KILLED IN HER TEMPORARY D.C.
HOME TWO YEARS AGO.
>> Nancy: A CRIME THAT
ROCKED THE DISTRICT.
NOW THE MAN ACCUSED IN HER
RAPE AND MURDER IS ON TRIAL.
D.C. BUREAU CHIEF SAM FORD IN
THE COURTROOM FOR TODAY'S
EMOTIONAL TESTIMONY.
SAM?
>> Sam: YES, NANCY, I HAVE
NEVER SEEN A TRIAL THAT HAD SO
MUCH, LET'S SAY MEDIA IN IT.
SURVEILLANCE MEDIA FROM
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO OF THE
POLICE ARRIVING ON THE SCENE,
FROM THE BODY CAM FOOTAGE TO
THE SUSPECT SUPPOSEDLY WALKING
AROUND THE NEIGHBORHOOD, TO
A.T.M.s.
A LOT OF MEDIA, WHICH IS
CERTAINLY BEING USED TO TRY TO
CONVINCE A JURY IN THIS CASE
INVOLVING THE HOMICIDE OF
34-YEAR-OLD H -- KARINA MEAL.
SHE WAS THREE DAYS SHORT OF
HER 35th BIRTHDAY WHEN THE
MAN SNATCHED HER LIFE AWAY,
SAID THE PROSECUTOR, POINTING
TO TROARE.
HE STABBED HER 40 TIMES AND
STOLE HER CAR.
THE MAN IN THE SURVEILLANCE
VIDEO, PROSECUTORS SAY, WENT
ON A SPENDING SPREE WITH HER
DEBIT AND THE CREDIT CARDS.
>> WE HAD DINNER TOGETHER
SUNDAY NIGHT.
>> MEL TALKED TO THE REPORTERS
AFTER THE MURDER TWO YEARS AGO
TESTIFIED TODAY HE FOUND THE
BODY.
HE WAS THE YOUNG ARTIST'S
BOSS.
THEY HAD COME FROM A PROGRAM
IN NORTH CAROLINA IN D.C. TO
WORK ON AN ART PROJECT.
WHEN MEAL FINISHED THE WORK,
SHE WAS HEADING HOME AND THEY
LEARNED SHE NEVER MADE IT OUT
OF THE BASEMENT APART WHEN
CHEN FOUND HER ON 14th
STREET NORTHEAST.
PROSECUTORS SAY THEY BELIEVE
TROARE ACCOSTED HER WHILE
PACKING THE CAR TO LEAVE.
HIS D.N.A. FOUND IN HER BODY.
HER FATHER RONALD MEAL
TESTIFIED HE WAS HOME IN
SEATTLE WHEN HE HEARD HIS
DAUGHTER WAS MISSING.
FRANTICALLY CALLING POLICE
AGENCIES FROM D.C. TO NORTH
CAROLINA FEARING SHE HAD AN
ACCIDENT AND WAS IN A
HOSPITAL.
BUT IT WAS MURDER.
DEFENSE ATTORNEY SAID MURDER,
BUT NOT BY TROARE.
NO BLOOD WAS FOUND ON HIS
CLOTHING.
THE D.N.A. CAN BE EXPLAINED,
OF COURSE, THE JURY AND
EVERYONE ELSE IS WAITING TO
FIND OUT WHAT THAT EXPLANATION
MIGHT BE.
WE WILL HAVE MORE COMING UP AT
5:00.
REPORTING LIVE FROM D.C.
SUPERIOR COURT, I'M SAM FORD,
ABC7 NEWS.
>> STORMWATCH7 WITH A WEATHER
ALERT NOW.
DANGEROUSLY WINDY DAY COMING
TO A CLOSE.
THIS TREE BROUGHT DOWN IN
FREDERICK, MARYLAND, SLAMMING
TO A HOME.
THANKFULLY NOBODY HURT THERE.
CHECK THIS OUT AT THE NATIONAL
AIRPORT.
WAIT FOR IT.
HERE IT COMES.
>> Bill: OH, OKAY.
>> Michelle: RIGHT?
THIS IS THE NATIONAL AIRPORT.
THE PLANES WERE WOBBLY COMING
IN.
THE PILOTS FORCE TO COME IN AT
AN ANGLE.
WHOA!
GOT TO HAVE A STRONG STOMACH
FOR THAT.
THEN STRAIGHTENING OUT AT THE
LAST SECOND.
NOW WITH CHIEF METEOROLOGIST
BILL KELLY.
I HAD TO HOLD ON TO MY POOCH.
HE IS ONLY A FEW POUNDS.
>> Bill: HE WOULD BE GONE
HAD YOU NOT.
I KNOW THE PILOTS ARE TRAINED
TO LAND LIKE THAT BUT IT'S
UNSETTLED.
>> Michelle: YOU CLUTCH THE
ARMREST TIGHT.
>> Bill: YOU DO!
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE
OVER THE TIDAL BASIN.
THE WAVES AND THE RIPPLES.
LOOKING AT NORTHWEST D.C., I
HAVE IT ZOOMED DOWN AND THE
TREES ARE SWAYING AROUND.
IT'S 37 IN D.C. NOW.
BUT WE ARE SEEING MORE 20s
THAN WE ARE SEEING 30s AND
40s AROUND THE REGION.
LOWER ON THE 61-MILE-PER-HOUR
GUSTS.
YESTERDAY THERE WAS AN
81-MILE-PER-HOUR GUST
REPORTED.
A LONG DURATION EVENT BUT IT
IS WINDING DOWN.
THE ONLY ADVISORY IS THIS ONE
HERE IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY AND
HOWARD COUNTY TO OUR AREA THEN
IT WILL GO UP NORTH.
CAROL COUNTY AND UP EAST.
THAT IS UNTIL 6:00 TONIGHT.
THE TEMPERATURES WILL GO DOWN.
THIS IS NOT BAD.
50 OR SO.
41 BY 8:00.
THIS IS DROPPING DOWN TO THE
FREEZING MARK BY TOMORROW
MORNING.
PROBABLY DOWN TO 31 WHEN IT IS
SAID AND DONE AS YOU HEAD OUT
THE DOOR AT 7:00.
WE WILL DO THE HOUR-BY-HOUR
FORECAST FOR THE WINDS.
THEY ARE CALMING DOWN.
IT WILL TAKE TIME.
WE HAVE THAT COMING UP IN A
FEW MINUTES.
>> Nancy: THANK YOU.
NOW TO A GROWING CONCERN ABOUT
THE DANGERS OF BLIND ZONES.
NOT THE ONES BEHIND YOUR
VEHICLE WE ALL WATCH OUT FOR.
BUT THE ONE IN FRONT OF IT.
>> Michelle: IF YOU HAVE AN
S.U.V., YOU ARE ESPECIALLY AT
RISK.
"7 ON YOUR SIDE" NATHAN BACA
SHOWS WHY THE BLIND ZONES HAVE
BECOME SO LARGE AND SO
DANGEROUS.
>> Nathan: STAN LAWLER LONG
THOUGHT HIS HIGH SEAT AND THE
WIDE BODY VEHICLE PROVIDED
ROOM WITH A VERY GOOD VIEW.
>> NICE TO HAVE THE VISIBILITY
SITTING UP HIGH.
>> Nathan: THEN HE REAL AS
ID EVERYTHING HE CAN'T SEE.
WHEN THE SIZE OF VEHICLES
BEGAN GROWING 20 YEARS AGO, SO
DID THE BLIND ZONES IN FRONT
OF THEM.
SOME STRETCH EIGHT FEET.
>> THERE IS A SIGNIFICANT
BLIND ZONE IN FRONT OF OUR
VEHICLES.
WE THIN■K ONCE WE GET IN ANDWE&,
>> THAT INVESTIGATION WILL
CONTINUE TONIGHT AT 6:00 ON
ABC7 NEWS.
>> Nancy: THAT IS
REMARKABLE.
I HAVE AN S.U.V.
THERE IS A FALSE SENSE OF
SECURITY.
HAVING NINE CHILDREN THAT
WOMAN DID NOT SPOT IS
REMARKABLE.
THE SON OF A PASTOR BLEEDING
GUILTY TO THE SEX CRIMES THAT
DATE BACK TO 2014.
[BRIEF PAUSE IN CAPTIONING]
>> Michelle: R. KELLY
ATTORNEY'S SPEAKING FOR HIM IN
COURT IN A NOT GUILTY PLEA ON
BEHALF OF THE R&B STAR FACING
TEN SEX CRIME CHARGES.
THIS IS AS AFFLALO
REPRESENTING TWO OF -- MICHAEL
AVENATTI REPRESENTING TWO OF
THE VICTIMS HAND OVER TAPES
THAT HE SAYS ARE EVIDENCE TO
POLICE.
KELLY IS HAVING TROUBLE
FINDING $100,000 TO POST BOND
REMAINS BEHIND BARS.
NEXT FOR US AT "ABC7 NEWS AT
4:00" --
FOLDABLE PHONES REALLY ARE THE
FUTURE.
TWO MORE ENTERS IN THE MARKET.
IF YOU THOUGHT THAT SAMSUNG'S
STARTING PRICE WAS HIGH, WAIT
UNTIL YOU SEE HUAWEI.
>> Nancy: MEASLES GONE FROM
THE COUNTRY NOW MAKING A
COMEBACK.
THE OUTBREAK STRETCHING COAST
TO COAST IS STILL AHEAD IN A
"7 ON Y
>> Nancy: HOW ABOUT THIS?
HUAWEI WITH ITS OWN FOLDABLE
FUN.
>> Michelle: THIS IS DAYS
AFTER SAMSUNG DID THE SAME
THING.
IT WILL BE 5G COMPATIBLE LIKE
SAMSUNDAY -- SAMSUNG.
BUT IT HAS PRICE TAG OF
$2,600, A FEW HUNDRED MORE
THAN SAMSUNG.
>> Nancy: I SAW SOMEONE ON
FACEBOOK SAID YOU COULD MAKE
ANY PHONE FOLDABLE IF YOU ARE
STRONG ENOUGH.
BUT FLIP PHONES APPARENTLY THE
FUTURE AGAIN.
L.G. WITH REVAMPED VERSION OF
THE DISCONTINUED LINE.
IT HAS TWO SCREENS THAT WORK
INDEPENDENTLY TO WATCH A MOVIE
ON ONE AND SURF THE WEB OR
TEXT ON THE OTHER.
TAP IN TO 5G NETWORKS.
STILL AHEAD AT "ABC7 NEWS AT
4:00" --
THE SEARCH FOR ANSWERS
FOLLOWING THE CARGO JET CRASH
OUTSIDE OF HOUSTON.
AS WE GET A NEW VIEW OF THE
FLIGHT'S FINAL MOMENTS.
>> Michelle: PLUS --
>> THAT CATAPULTED OUR WORK TO
OVER 50 MILLION VIEWS.
USING THE FAME TO HELP THE
NEXT GENERATION OF DANCERS.
ABC7 CELEBRATING BLACK HISTORY
MONTH WITH THE SISTERS TAPPING
IN AN AFRICAN-AMERICAN ART
FORM.
>> Nancy: LOOKING FORWARD TO
THAT.
THERE IS STILL TIME TO VOTE IN
THE ABC7 INSTAPOLL.
GO TO WJLA.com/VoteNow TO
LET US KNOW IF YOU WOULD GO TO
THE INDEPENDENCE DAY PARTY
HOSTED BY PRESIDENT TRUMP ON
THE MALL.
WE WILL CHECK THE RESULT AFTER
THE BREAK.
UPDATE LIVE
I love my babies,
love my boys.
Since I'm a truck driver,
you know there's times
that I'm gone for,
like, three weeks at a time.
Even if I'm 3,000 miles away,
I'm connected with my boys.
Every day I can
video chat with them.
I could be in the middle
of Wyoming.
Even if I'm like waaay...
out here,
I can still reach my kids.
Baby, you-- you see me?
(sons)
Hey, Daddy!
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now comes with Apple Music on us
and $300 off our best phones.
Only on Verizon.
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
>> Michelle: TWO SISTERS
FROM D.C. MAKING THEIR MARK IN
THE WORLD OF TAP DANCING.
A DANCE STYLE WITH A COME LEX
HISTORY DATING BACK 300 YEARS
TO THE FIRST ENSLAVED PEOPLE
BROUGHT TO THE U.S. FROM WEST
AFRICA.
INSPIRED BY AFRICAN-AMERICAN
TAP DANCING ICONS AS CHILDREN,
THEY ARE NOW USING THEIR STAR
POWER TO HELP THE NEXT
GENERATION LEARN THE MAGIC OF
TAP.
>> UNDER ALL OF THAT
OPPRESSION AND ABUSE AND RAPE,
THEY WERE CREATING TO SURVIVE.
SO THAT IS WHAT MAKES IT SO
POWERFUL TO BE A TAP DANCER.
>> Michelle: MUSIC MADE FOR
MOVEMENT.
FIERCE FOOTWORK FROM A FEEL
TAP DANCE BAND.
THIS IS JUST A WARMUP FOR THE
GROUP "SYNCOPATED LADIES."
THE HIGH ENERGY AND GOALS
EMBRACED BY BEYONCÉ.
♪ ♪
>> SHE SHARED OUR VIDEO.
SHE PUT IT ON BEYONCÉ.com
FOR WEEKS.
>> SHE CREATED IT IN 2003.
SHE AND HER SISTER THRILLED TO
PERFORM IN D.C., THE CITY THAT
MADE THEM.
AND TAUGHT THEM THE IMPORTANCE
OF HARD WORK THROUGH PROGRAMS
AT THE KENNEDY CENTER IN
WASHINGTON PERFORMING ARTS
SOCIETY, THEY WERE INSPIRED BY
TAP LEGENDS.
>> GREGORY HINES WOULD COME
OFTEN.
NICHOLAS BROTHERS ALSO CAME
HERE TO D.C.
AND JUST TO SEE THE ICONS.
WOW!
I SAW THIS AMAZING ARTIST, YOU
KNOW ON THE BIG SCREEN.
NOW I SEE THEM IN PERSON.
AND THEY'RE NICE!
IT CONNECTED US TO MAKING THIS
IDEA REAL.
>> Michelle: THOSE ARE SOME
OF THE GREATS TWO PAVEED THE
WAY.
THE A.K.A. MASTER JUVA,
POPULAR IN THE 1840s.
MANY SAY HE PUT TAP ON THE MAP
AS A THEATRICAL ART FORM.
MOVES COPIED BY WHITE DANCERS
LATER USED BY TROUPES.
>> WE ARE LIVING IN THE STEM
OF THE ANCESTOR AND CREATING
OUR OWN STEP.
>> THEIR OWN STEP IN THEIR OWN
SHOES.
>> WE ARE THE FIRST BACK WOMEN
TO HAVE A SHOE DEAL.
THESE ARE OUR TAP SHOES.
THEY ARE CALLED CHLOE TAP
SHOES.
>> MENTORS LIKE DEBBIE ALLEN
GUIDING THEM THROUGH FILM
SCHOOL AT COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY.
THEY HAVE PERFORMED IN 30
COUNTRIES, SHARING THE JOY OF
TAP.
>> TAP DANCING IS AMAZING.
IT'S AN AFRICAN-AMERICAN ART
FORM AND IMPROVISATIONAL IN
THE TRUEST ESSENCE SO YOU
CREATE AGAINST THE ODDS,
CREATING MAGIC IS WHAT WE
REPRESENT.
>> Michelle: THEY
ACKNOWLEDGE THE IMPORTANCE OF
THE MENTORS IN THEIR LIFE AND
SAY THE MISSION NOW IS TO BE
MENTORS TO THE NEXT GENERATION
OF TAP DANCERS.
THEY RUN THE TAP FESTIVAL AND
THIS APRIL IS THE 11th
YEAR.
WE HAVE DETAILS ABOUT THAT AND
HOW TO REGISTER ON WJLA.com.
>> Nancy: THANK YOU.
GREAT STORY.
THE C.D.C. CALLING IT WORST
MEASLES OUTBREAK IN YEARS.
159 CONFIRMED CASES SINCE THE
START OF THE NEW YEAR.
THEY SPANNED TEN STATUTES FROM
-- TEN STATES FROM COAST
TO COAST.
THEY ARE RECOMMENDING THE
VACCINE THEY SAY IS 97%
EFFECTIVE.
VIDEO APPEARING TO SHOW THE
FINAL MOMENTS OF A DOOMED
CARGO JET FLIGHT AS IT
APPROACHED HOUSTON.
THE BOEING 767 CARGO JET
CONTRACTED BY AMAZON'S PRIME
AIR WENT DOWN ON SATURDAY.
TWO OF THE THREE CREW MEMBERS
HAVE BEEN RECOVERED.
TRANSPORTATION OFFICIALS ARE
SEARCHING NOW FOR THE
SO-CALLED BLACK BOXES THAT
WILL CONTAIN THE FLIGHT DATA
RECORDERS AND THE COCKPIT
VOICE RECORDINGS.
AND CHECK THIS OUT, UNWANTED
GUEST PUTTING A CALIFORNIA
NEIGHBORHOOD ON LOCKDOWN.
BIG CAT THERE.
THE HOME SECURITY CAMERAS HAVE
PEOPLE LOOKING OUT THEIR
WINDOWS CAPTURING A MOUNTAIN
LION.
MAKING ITSELF AT HOME RIGHT IN
THEIR YARD.
>> THEN I ASKED MY HUSBAND IF
HE THOUGHT THE MOUNTAIN LION
COULD SIT IN THE DOG DOOR.
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT THAT, TOO.
>> Nancy: GOOD QUESTION.
PEOPLE BLOCKED OFF THE
NEIGHBORHOOD WHILE THE ANIMAL
CONTROL TRANQUILIZED THE CAT
AND THE ANIMAL RELEASED BACK
IN THE WILD FAR FROM THE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> Michelle: THAT WAS CLOSE.
THE OSCARS ARE OVER BUT THE
CHATTER ISN'T.
DOMINATING SOCIAL MEDIA FROM
CRITICISM OF THE PICKS TO THE
LADY GAGA-BRADLEY COOP
COOPER -- COOPER ROMANCE
RUMORS.
LINDSEY MASTIS HAS A LOOK.
>> Lindsey: THE DUET HAS A
LOT OF PEOPLE TWEETING THESE
TWO ARE SO IN LOVE!
NOW, LET'S REMEMBER.
COOPER BROUGHT HIS GIRLFRIEND
TO THE OSCARS AND SHE AND LADY
GAGA HUGGED AT ONE POINT.
MOVING ON.
WE HAVE OLIVIA COLEMAN
STEALING THE SHOW.
SHE WON FOR BEST ACTRESS FOR
"THE FAVOURITE."
HER SPEECH WAS ENDEARING TO
GIVE SHOUT OUT TO GLENN CLOSE
AND LADY GAGA.
AND TWITTER NOTICED THIS.
MALIK TOOK A TUMBLE ON THE
STAGE AFTER GETTING HIS AWARD.
PARAMEDICS CHECKED HIM OUT AND
HE IS FINE.
AND THE SPIKE LEA'S FIRST WIN
FOR "BlacKkKlansman."
THE SPEECH WAS POLITICAL AND
TRUMP CALLED AT IT RACIST HIT
ON THE PRESIDENT AND WRITING
IN PART HE HAS DONE MORE FOR
AFRICAN-AMERICANS THAN ANY
OTHER PRESIDENT.
BUT THE BIGGEST UPSET IS
"GREEN BOOK" WINNING FOR BEST
PICTURE.
SOME THINK IT'S A GREAT
CHOICE.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE SOUNDING
OFF TWEETING THAT "BLACK
PANTHER" SHOULD HAVE WON.
FOR THE FACT THAT THERE WAS NO
HOST THIS YEAR.
PEOPLE SEEMED TO LIKE THAT.
ONE CALLING IT THE HOSTLESS
WITH THE MOSTESS.
BACK TO YOU.
>> Nancy: ALL RIGHT.
LET'S LOOK AGAIN AT THE
INSTAPOLL.
RIGHT THERE.
WITH THE VOTE OF 80% SO FAR,
MAJORITY OF YOU SAY YOU WILL
NOT GO TO THE PRESIDENT
4th OF JULY CELEBRATION IF
HE HOSTS HIS OWN ON THE MALL.
WE WILL KEEP THE POLL OPEN.
HEAD TO WJLA.com/VoteNow.
AT 5:00, TOM ROUSSEY IS
COVERING THIS STORY, ASKING
PEOPLE AROUND HERE IF THE
PRESIDENT'S PLANS WOULD ADD TO
OR DISTRACT FROM ONE OF D.C.'S
LONGEST STANDING TRADITIONS.
>> Michelle: TAKE A LOOK AT
THIS.
THE ABC7 VIEWER PANEL IN --
PAM IN ROCKVILLE SENDING US
BEAUTIFUL PICTURES OF A
RAINBOW THAT SHE TOOK AFTER
THE STORMS CLEARED OUT
YESTERDAY.
IT WENT IN THROUGH
WJLA.com/CHIMEIN OR TAPPING
"CHIME IN" ON THE ABC7 NEWS
APP.
WE WILL SHARE PICTURES ON AIR
AND IN A GALLERY ONLINE.
SO PRETTY!
>> Bill: BEAUTIFUL!
>> Michelle: NICE TO SEE.
>> Nancy: LOOK BEHIND US.
NATIONAL HARBOR, SO WINDY OUT
THERE.
YOU HAVE TO HOLD ON TO YOUR
HAT.
>> Bill: YOU DO.
WIND ADVISORY FOR THE MOST
PART IS GONE.
STILL LINGERING IN NORTHERN
MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
OTHERWISE IT'S BREEZY.
WINDY.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
BUT BELOW ADVISORY CRITERIA.
THE WINDS WILL CALM DOWN
SIGNIFICANTLY IN A FEW HOURS.
I WILL SHOW YOU THAT IN A
MOMENT.
IN NORTHWEST D.C., 50 DEGREES.
WINDS AT 24 MILES PER HOUR
SUSTAINED.
GUSTS TO 35.
SAME WITH GERMANTOWN.
THE LAST READING WAS AROUND 29
MILES PER HOUR.
AT 44 DEGREES.
42 IN HAGERSTOWN.
BUT LOOK AT THE BEAUTIFUL BLUE
SKY.
THE AIR IS NICE AND CLEAN.
IT'S WINDY.
THE WINDS CLEAN THINGS OUT SO
THAT IS GOOD.
LOOKING AT THE CURRENT WIND
GUSTS AROUND THE AREA.
THIS MAP LOOKS DIFFERENT THAN
IT DID SEVERAL HOURS AGO.
36 MILES PER HOUR.
THAT IS YOUR CURRENT WIND GUST
IN WINCHESTER.
37 IN CUMBERLAND.
SAME WITH D.C.
25 QUANTICO.
22-MILE-PER-HOUR WIND GUST FOR
FREDERICKSBURG.
AS WE GO TO THE EVENING, LET
ME ADVANCE TO 8:00.
YOU ARE GOING TO NOTICE A
DRAMATIC DECREASE BE THE WINDS
RIGHT NOW ARE GUSTING 25 TO
40.
IN A FEW HOURS WITH THE RARE
EXCEPTION OF A COUPLE OF
PLACES MAINLY BACK WEST, YOU
WILL HAVE VERY LIGHT TO 20,
25-MILE-PER-HOUR GUSTS.
WE GET DEEPER IN THE NIGHT,
11:00, IT WINDS DOWN AND VERY
FEW WIND GUSTS THROUGH THE
OVERNIGHT HOURS AND IN THE
MORNING TOMORROW.
IN TERMS OF THE SKY, AS I
MENTION, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
NOT JUST HERE BUT AROUND THE
REGION.
YOU HAVE TO GO WELL NORTH TO
SEE ANY CLOUDS.
OF COURSE, SNOW.
BUT IF YOU HAVE TRAVEL PLANS
TONIGHT, GOING WEST, EAST OR
SOUTH, I MEAN THERE IS HARDLY
ANY CLOUD COVER AT ALL.
IT'S LOOKING GOOD.
FUTURE CAST WILL KEEP IT THAT
WAY THROUGHOUT THE EVENING.
YOU COMBINE THAT WITH THE
REDEGREES IN WINDS AND THAT IS
RECIPE FOR THE CHILLY
TEMPERATURES.
24 TO 25.
SOME OF THE COOLER SPOTS TO
31.
MAYBE 32 FOR D.C.
START OUT WITH THE SUNSHINE.
A FEW CLOUDS ON THE INCREASE
IN THE AFTERNOON.
IT'S JUST CLOUD COVER.
I DON'T EXPECT RAIN AND/OR
SNOW OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
NOT A BAD DAY.
THE TEMPERATURE UP TO 50 FOR
TUESDAY.
WE WILL SEE THE NUMBERS CLIMB
FROM 32 AT 6:00 A.M. TO 48 BY
THIS TIME TOMORROW.
48 AT 3:00 SPECIFICALLY.
NANCY OVER TO YOU.
>> Nancy: BILL, THANK YOU.
BY THE WAY, I WANT TO TAKE A
MOMENT TO THANK CYCLE FOR
SURVIVAL FOR INVITING ME TO
TAKE PART IN THE GROUP RIDE IN
BETHESDA YESTERDAY.
SINCE THEY WERE FOUNDED IN
2007, CYCLE FOR SURVIVAL HAS
RAISED MORE THAN $200 MILLION
FOR RARE CANCER RESEARCH.
THAT IS ME SITTING WITH THE
POM-POM.
THEY WILL BE HOLDING THE D.C.
EVENT THIS UPCOMING WEEKEND.
SO IF YOU WANT MORE
INFORMATION YOU CAN GO TO THE
FACEBOOK PAGE TO FIND A LINK.
WE'LL BE R
♪ We buy any car dot com ♪
♪ we buy any car dot com ♪
♪ ANY ANY ANY ANY ♪
Did you know trading in your car
at a dealer could cost
you money?
A recent study found consumers
who trade in their car
pay an average of $990
dollars more.
So don't trade in...
sell it....
to We Buy Any Car.
Learn more and get your free
online valuation
now at we buy any car dot com
♪ Find out how much your car is
worth at WeBuyAnyCar.com ♪
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
MINNESOTA --
>> Michelle: A FUEL SPILL
FIRST SPOTTED BY SOMEONE
FISHING IN THE AREA AND CARL
WILLIS HAS ENVIRONMENTAL
CONCERNS.
>> THERE WERE PEOPLE THAT
COULD SEE THIS FROM FAR AWAY.
YOU CAN SEE IT WASHING DOWN
THE ENTIRE CANAL.
>> Carl: APPARENT FUEL SPILL
SENDING CONCERN FOR THOSE WHO
LIVE AND FISH ON FOUR MILE
RUN.
THE FIRST REPORT STARTED TO
COME IN THURSDAY WHEN THE
RIVER KEEPERS SAY THE FUMES
WERE SO STRONG THAT ANGLERS
WERE TOLD TO EVACUATE THE
AREA.
>> THIS IS WHAT WE LIVE OFF
OF.
THIS FLOWS IN THE POTOMAC.
EVERYONE SHOULD BE CONCERNED
WITH THE CHEMICALS GETTING IN
THE WATER WAYS.
>> Carl: THE CONCERN IS THE
LOOK OF RESPONSE.
THE RIVERKEEPER TELLS ME THAT
THE FIRE CREWS PUT OUT BOONS
TO ABSORB THE MATERIAL.
BUT HE STILL HAS CONCERNS.
>> WHO WILL FOLLOW UP AND
REMOVE THE BOOMS BEFORE
THEY'RE WASHED DOWNSTREAM WITH
THE OIL?
RIGHT NOW THEY ARE A HAZARDOUS
MATERIAL.
>> Carl: HE TRACKED IT TO
UPSTREAM BUT MY MONDAY
AFTERNOON HE SAYS HE STILL HAD
NOT SEEN OR HEARD FROM THE
VIRGINIA DEPARTMENT OF
ENVIRONMENTAL QUALITY.
>> I'M CURIOUS WHY VIRGINIA
D.E.Q. STILL HAS NOT COME OUT
TO THE SCENE, TO MY KNOWLEDGE
OR CONTACTED THE NETWORK.
>> EVEN A STATEMENT WOULD BE
GREAT.
SOMETHING TO TELL US WHAT THEY
KNOW ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED.
>> Carl: WE CALLED AND
E-MAILED THE VIRGINIA D.E.Q.
AS WELL.
WE HAVE NOT HEARD FROM THEM.
WE WILL LET YOU KNOW IF WE DO
HEAR FROM THEM AND WHY THERE
IS A CONCERN THAT IT WILL ONLY
MAKE THE MATTERS WORSE.
THAT IS SOMETHING WE ARE
WORKING ON FOR 6:00.
CARL WILLIS, ABC7 NEWS.
>> Jonathan: HAPPENING NOW
AT 5:00, A HOME SLICED IN
HALF, ROADS BLOCK AND
THOUSANDS WITHOUT POWER.
A CLOSE CALL.
>> HAD IT FALL ON THE THE
FRONT OF THE VEHICLE, WE
WOULDN'T BE HERE TODAY.
>> Jonathan: ABC7 SURVEYING
THE WIND DAMAGE ACROSS THE
D.M.V.
>>> A TEACH EARS AIDE TRYING
TO SKIRT THE CAMERA --
TEACHER'S AIDE TRYING TO SKIRT
THE CAMERA AND FACING CRUELTY
CHARGE.
AND THE STUDENT WAS A SPECIAL
NEEDS STUDENT.
>> A CLOSELY HELD SECRET.
A CLASSICAL TALENT THAT MADE
THE TEACHERS AND THE
CLASSMATES' JAWS DROP.
>> Announcer: NOW "ABC7 NEWS
AT 5:00".
ON YOUR SIDE.
>> RIGHT NOW AT 5:00, A
DANGEROUS CLOSE CALL.
LOOK AT THIS.
WIND RIPPING DOWN A
TRANSFORMER CRUSHING A CAR AS
TWO PEOPLE WERE INSIDE.
>> Alison: THAT DAMAGE IS
FAR FROM ISOLATED.
ALL ACROSS THE D.M.V., THE
STORMWATCH7 WEATHER TEAM ARE
TRACKING DOWNED TREES AND
THOUSANDS OF POWER OUTAGES.
WE HAVE TEAM COVERAGE TONIGHT.
IE