REALTIME CLOSED CAPTIONING
PROVIDED BY
U.S. CAPTIONING COMPANY.
>> A SOGGY SATURDAY.
FAST MOVING STRONG STORMS
SWEEPING THROUGH THE AREA.
WE'RE NOT DONE YET.
TEAM COVERAGE TONIGHT.
CONDITIONS IN CALIFORNIA.
DAMAGE DONE AFTER TWO EARTH
QUAKE HIT AND THE THE
DESPERATE MEASURES SOME ARE
TAKING TO STAY SAFE.
EXPLOSION LEVELS A FLORIDA
SHOPPING CENTER.
WHAT SOME HAD TO DO TO GET
TO SAFETY AND WHAT WE'RE
LEARNING ABOUT THE SHOCKING
SCENE TONIGHT.
>> Announcer: NOW ABC 7
NEWS AT 11:00 ON YOUR SIDE.
>> Anchor: BOOMING THUNDER
, BOLTS OF LIGHTNING,
AN ACTIVE EVENING ACROSS THE
AREA.
WE HAD THE HEAT AND HUMIDITY
THAT TURNED INTO RAIN AND
STORMS IN A MATTER OF HOURS.
LIVE LOOK AT RADAR AND STILL
SEEING ACTIVITY MOVING
THROUGH.
THAT INCLUDES A LOT OF LIGHT
NING, WE'VE TEAM
COVERAGE TONIGHT FROM THE
DAMAGE WE SPOTTED WHILE ON
THE ROADWAYS TO WHEN WE CAN
EXPECT THE RAIN TO MOVE OUT.
I'M HERE WITH BRIAN van de
Graaff, YOU'VE BEEN BUSY
ALL DAY LONG.
>> WE DID GET STORMS EARLY.
A FEW IN THE MOUNTAINS BUT
AROUND 7:30 WE GET BIG ONES.
TALK ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED OUT
THERE EARLIER.
WE THINK WHEN YOU SHARE YOUR
PHOTOS WITH US, THIS IS FROM
STEVEN.
SEE THE KENNEDY CENTER.
LOOK AT THE BOLT OF
LIGHTNING OFF IN THE
DISTANCE.
COOL SHOT OUT.
THERE LUCKILY NO ONE WAS
INJURED.
THE SHOT FROM MR. FUN GUY
ACROSS THE WATER.
NICE LIGHTNING BOLT.
ANOTHER THING WES INNED WERE
THE WINDS.
WE HAD GUSTS RATHER IMPRESS
IVE IN THE SEVERE
CATEGORY.
66 MILE PER HOUR GUST REPORT
ED OVER AT NATS PARK
AND 58 UP AT H.U.IN
NORTHWEST D.C.
ANNAPOLIS PICKED UP A 2 MILE
AN HOUR AND REAGAN NATIONAL
HAD A 37 MERLE WIND GUST.
MUGGY AND MILD THROUGH THE
NEXT COUPLE OF HOURS.
TEMPERATURES HOVER IN THE 70
s, WE COULD SEE PATCHY
FOG SETTLE IN TOWARDS DAWN
TOMORROW.
COUPLE OF POCKETS OF RAIN
FROM HEAVY, ALLEN FRESH WITH
HEAVY RAIN.
MECHANICVILLE, HUGHS VILLE
LOTS OF LIGHTNING IN THE
DISTANCE.
THE LAST BATCH WILL DRIFT
OFF AND BLIND IT A LITTLE
BIT AFTER BREAK, A LOOK AT
THE LATEST FUTURE CAST AND
TALK ABOUT DRYER MORE
COMFORTABLE AIR IN STORE FOR
THE START OF EARLY NEXT WEEK
CARL.
>> Anchor: TONIGHT'S
STORMS COMING WITH STRONG
WINDS THIS LED TO DAMAGE IN
THE DISTRICT.
VICTORIA SANCHEZ CONTINUES
LIVE TEAM COVERAGE FROM
MOBILE TRACK AND WHAT ARE
YOU SEEING TONIGHT?
>> Reporter: MUCH
DIFFERENT SCENE FROM JUST A
FEW HOURS AGO.
WE'RE IN NORTHWEST
WASHINGTON AND LET ME SHOW
YOU WHAT WE'RE LOOKING AT.
A FEW SPRINKLES, WE'RE SEE
ING SOME LIGHTNING IN THE
DISTANCE SO THAT IS HANGING
AROUND THE D.M.V.AREA.
IN A FEW HOURS AGO THE WIND
CAME THROUGH KNOCKING DOWN
TREES AND BUILDING MATERIAL
FROM ROOFS.
AS THE STORM MOVED INTO THE
DISTRICT VISIBILITY ALONG
CANAL ROAD DROPPED AS SHEETS
OF RAIN CAME DOWN FAST.
THE ROAD QUICKLY STARTED TO
FLOOD AND SOME CARS PULLED
TO THE SIDE TO LET THE STORM
PASS BEFORE DRIVING AGAIN.
ONCE THE RAIN STOPPED
NEIGHBORS ALONG THE 1900
BLOCK OF 38th STREET
NORTHWEST WENT OUT TO SEE
THE DAMAGE.
>> WE WERE WATCHING AT THE
BACK WINDOW.
WE WERE' DUMB FOUNDED BY THE
SUDDENNESS WHICH IT OCCURRED
AN THE FEROCITY OF IT.
SO WE'RE REALLY STUCK WATCH
ING T.V.
>> Reporter: A LARGE TREE
SPLIT IN HALF AND CRASHED
DOWN ON PARKED CARS.
>> CLOSE TO MY SON'S HOME ON
HIS CAR ON HIS NEIGHBOR'S
CAR.
>> Reporter: BOB IS VISIT
ING HIS SON'S FAMILY IN
NORTHWEST AND SAID LUCKILY
NO ONE WAS HURT.
THE NEIGHBORHOOD WAS WITHOUT
ELECTRICITY AS LIMBS BROUGHT
DOWN POWER LINES, ALSO IN
NORTHWEST ON 29100 OF 4th
STREET PALLETS OF BUILDING
MATERIALS BLEW OFF AN APART
MENT BUILDING.
ONE MAN WAS INJURED FROM THE
FLYING DEBRIS.
WE WERE ON CANAL ROAD WHEN
THE STORM CAME THROUGH, AND
IT WAS QUITE A SCENE.
WE ACTUALLY SAW THE SHEET OF
RAIN THAT SEPARATED THE DRY
ROAD FROM THE SUPER SLICK
ROAD WHEN WE HEADED INTO
MARYLAND.
OUT RIGHT NOW IT'S STARTING
TO CLEAR UP.
SO HOPEFULLY SMOOTH SAILING
FOR ANY PLANS TOMORROW.
VICTORIA SANCHEZ, ABC 7 NEWS
>> Anchor: THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
TONIGHT'S STORMS AND WINDS
LEADING TO POWER OUTAGES IN
PARTS OF THE AREA.
THESE NUMBERS JUST IN.
BIG JUMP IN ARLINGTON UNDER
A FAIRFAX.
FAIRFAX HAS THE MOST
OUTTAGES WITH MORE THAN 3600
PEOPLE WITHOUT POWER TONIGHT
AND IN ARLINGTON, 2600 OUT
AGES.
NEARLY 2,000 CUSTOMERS IN
PRINCE GEORGES COUNTY IN THE
DARK TONIGHT AND THERE ARE
COMBINED 860 OUTAGES BETWEEN
D.C.AND MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
LOUDOUN COUNTY IS SEEING
OVER 1,000 POWER OUTTAGES
RIGHT NOW.
IN ARLINGTON, CREWS BATTLING
TWO SEPARATE HOUSE FIRES
TONIGHT.
BOTH CAUSED BY LIGHTNING
STRIKES.
THE FIRES ARE OUT NOW AND NO
ONE WAS HURT.
IN BOTH CASES FIREFIGHTERS
SAY LIGHTNING HIT THE ROOF
AND SPARKED A FIRE IN THE
ATTIC.
TOMORROW EXPECTED TO BE
ANOTHER HOT ONE WHICH MEANS
THE MAYOR COULD ACTIVATE THE
DISTRICT'S HEAT EMERGENCY
PLAN.
IF SO THAT MEANS COOLING
CENTERS WILL BE OPEN FOR
THOSE NEEDING A BREAK FROM
THE SUN.
YOU CAN TRACK THE HEAT AND
SEE WHEN RAIN SHOWERS COULD
BE HEADING TO YOUR
NEIGHBORHOOD.
DOWNLOAD THE FREE STORM
WATCH 7 APP.
>> LET'S GO!
>> WE CONTINUE TO GATHER
VIDEO OUT OF CALIFORNIA
WHERE RESIDENTS ARE BRACING
FOR MORE AFTERSHOCKS
FOLLOWING TWO POWERFUL EARTH
QUAKES.
STRONG TREMORS AND LIGHTS
TRIGGER IN WHAT LOOKS LIKE A
SECURE REEL SCENE.
ITEMS KNOCKED OFF THE
SHELVES THERE AND DANGER
THAT HEAVY APPLIANCES COULD
BE KNOCKED ON TO THE AISLES.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
THE SHAKING WAS SO BAD IN
THE CITY OF RIDGECREST THE
WATER IN THE POOL JOLTS BACK
AND FORTH CREATING LARGE
WAVES AND THE WATER SPLASH
ING OUT OF THE POOL.
TONIGHT THERE IS FEAR MORE
EARTHQUAKES COULD BE ON THE
WAY.
THE NUMBER OF AFTERSHOCKS
NUMBER IN THE THOUSANDS.
PAUL IS LIVE IN RIDGECREST
WITH THE MAJOR ANNOUNCEMENT
FROM CALIFORNIA'S GOVERNOR.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> Reporter: YOU HAD AN
EMERGENCY DECLARATION HERE
IN CALIFORNIA AS YOU LOOK
BEHIND ME.
A QUIET WITH SOME OF THE
BUSINESSES.
YOU ARTICULATED ABOUT THE
AFTERSHOCKS.
THIS POPULAR RESTAURANT
QUIET AND DARK ON A SATURDAY
NIGHT.
JUST SO MANY AFTERSHOCKS TO
RECKON WITH IN THE RIDGE
CREST AREA.
PANIC AS A SECOND MAJOR
EARTHQUAKE HIT CALIFORNIA
FRIDAY NIGHT.
11 TIMES STRONGER THAN THE
FIRST.
>> THE LAST ONE WAS MORE
QUICK, FASTER AND LASTED
LONGER.
>> Reporter: AUTHORITIES
SAY THE QUAKE TRIGGERED GAS
LEAKS AND STRUCTURE FIRES.
ROCK SLIDES SHUT DOWN STATE
ROAD 78 AND THE GOVERNOR RE
MAINS OPTIMISTIC ABOUT
EFFORTS MOVING FORWARD.
>> I HAVE NO TREPIDATION
ABOUT THIS COMMUNITY BUILD
ING STRONGER AND IN
TIME, THAT WILL SHOCK YOU.
>> Reporter: OFFICIALS SAY
THERE ARE NO FATALITIES OR
MAJOR INJURIES, POWER HAS
BEEN RESTORED TO MOST
CUSTOMERS.
AND MANY MAJOR STORES ARE
NOW OPEN.
NOW DAMAGE ASSESSMENT TEAMS
AND STRUCTURAL ENGINEERS ARE
ON THE GROUND.
>> THAT'S TO GO IN UNDER A
LOOK AT LITTLE MORE GRAND
LAR REVIEW OF THE DAMAGE.
>> Reporter: CALIFORNIA
RESIDENTS ARE WARNED TO BE
READY FOR ANOTHER EVENT.
>> IT'S IMPERATIVE THAT YOU
ARE PREPARED NO MATTER WHERE
YOU ARE.
>> Reporter: SPEAKING
THOSE EVENTS THE
SEISMOLOGIST LUKEY JONES
FROM SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA SAY
S THERE HAVE BEEN 3,000
EARTHQUAKES ASSOCIATED WITH
THIS HIGH VALLEY EVENT.
BACK TO YOU.
>> Anchor: SOME FAMILIES
ARE SO AFRAID OF THE AFTER
SHOCKS THEY ARE SLEEP
ING OUTSIDE.
ONE FATHER SAID HE HAD A
CLOSE CALL WITH HIS WIFE AND
CHILDREN WITH DEBRIS NEARLY
FALLING ON THEM AND DOESN'T
WANT TO RISK IT AGAIN SO THE
FAMILY IS CAMPING OUTSIDE OF
THEIR OWN HOME.
THE QUAKE WAS SO POWERFUL
THEY FELT IT IN LAS VEGAS
DURING THE SUMMER LEAGUE
GAMES.
IT HIT DURING THE FOURTH
QUARTER.
THE SCOREBOARD STARTED SWAY
ING AND OFFICIALS DECID
ED TO STOP THE GAME.
THE FOLLOWING GAME CANCELLED
ALL TOGETHER.
NEW DETAILS ON THE EXPLOSION
THAT LEVELED A SOUTH FLORIDA
SHOPPING PLAZA.
AT LEAST 23 PEOPLE WERE
INJURED IN THE BLAST.
IT WAS CAUSED BY A GAS LEAK.
WITNESSES SAY PEOPLE INSIDE
OF AN L.A.FITNESS RACED TO
GET OUT TO GET TO SAFETY.
>> THE INSIDE OF THE STORE
CAVED?
>> I WENT IN MY CAR.
IT WAS LIKE RAINING BIG
PIECES OF THE ROOF, WALL,
EVERYTHING.
>> Anchor: ONCE IT WAS
DEEMED SAFE ENOUGH CREWS AND
RESCUE DOGS SEARCHED THROUGH
THE DEBRIS TO LOOK FOR
ANYONE WHO MAY HAVE BEEN
TRAPPED.
THE A.T.F.AND THE SHERIFF'S
BOMB SQUAD ARE ON THE SCENE
INVESTIGATING.
WE'VE LEARNED NO ONE WAS
TRAPPED OR SERIOUSLY HURT
FOLLOWING AN EXPLOSION THAT
ROCKED THE CAMPUS AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF NEVADA RENO.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> WE HAVE TO GO.
>> Anchor: THE BLAST
HAPPENED IN THE BOILER ROOM
OF ONE OF THE UNIVERSITY'S
DORM BUILDINGS.
TECHNICIANS WERE WORKING.
SEARCH DOGS FOUND NO ONE
TRAPPED INSIDE.
THIS EXPLOSION IS BEING CALL
ED A UTILITIES ACCIDENT.
STUDENTS WHO LIVE IF THE
DORMS ARE BEING MOVED TO A
NEARBY BUILDINGS WHILE RE
PAIRS ARE MADE.
FAR LEFT AND FAR RIGHT HELD
DUELING RALLIES TODAY.
THE FREE SPEECH RALLY HAPPEN
ED IN FREEDOM PLAZA
WHILE COUNTERPROTESTORS SET
UP NEXT DOOR.
BOTH PROTESTS REMAINED
PEACEFUL EVEN AS SOME MARCH
ED THROUGH THE GLEETS
WHEN ALL THESE DIFFERENT
DISCRIMINATIONS ARE GIVEN A
PLATFORM ALLIES HAVE TO COME
OUT AND THE SAY YOU ARE
SILENCED.
YOU DO NOT HAVE SPACE HERE.
>> I THINK THE FIRST
AMENDMENT IS VERY CRITICAL.
RIGHT THAT WE HAVE AS
AMERICANS, WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO SEE WHAT WE WANT AND TALK
WHAT WE WANT.
>> BOTH SIDES OF THE PROTEST
APPEARED TO HAVE EQUAL TURN
OUT.
WE RECEIVER NEW VIOLENT
CLASHES.
COMING UP ON ABC 7 NEWS AT
11:00 THE WILD AFTERMATH OF
A ROAD RAGE SHOOTING CAUGHT
ON CAMERA.
THE ONE THING THAT
INVESTIGATORS WANT THE
PUBLIC TO WATCH OUT FOR TO
HELP FIND THE SUSPECT.
A MAJOR WIN FOR SPACE X.
THE NEW VIDEO THE COMPANY RE
LEASED FROM ITS LATEST
LAUNCH AND WHAT THIS MEANS
FOR THE FUTURE OF SPACE EX
PLORATION.
>> Reporter: SHOWERS AND
RIBS TAPER BUT HEAVY DOWN
POURS, WE'LL TRACK THAT
AND LOOK AHEAD TO THE
SECONDS HALF 69 WEEKEND, CAN
YOU PUT YOUR UMBRELLAS
>> Announcer: YOU ARE
WATCHING ABC 7 NEWS AT 11:00
ON YOUR SIDE.
>> Anchor: RIGHT NOW A MAN
HUNT UNDER WAY IN HOUSTON
FOR THE ROAD RAGE SUSPECTED
WHO OPENED FIRE ON A FAMILY
ON THE FOURTH OF JULY.
THE GUNNIFY SET OFF FIRE
WORKS IN THE FAMILY'S
CAR AND THAT LED TO A FIERY
EXPLOSION.
YOU SEE IT THERE.
POLICE SAY THE DRIVER OF A
WHITE S.U.V. FOLLOWED THE
FAMILY INTO A GAS STAY, WHEN
THEY TRIED TO GET AWAY THE
DRIVER FIRED SHOTS.
THE PARENTS AND TWO TODDLERS
REMAIN IN THE HOSPITAL
TONIGHT.
A POOL PARTY TURNED INTO A
CRIME SCENE HOURS AGO IN
GLENN BURNIE.
POLICE SAY THEY GOT A SHOTS
FIRED CALL AND WHEN THEY
ARRIVED THEY DISCOVERED THEE
PEOPLE WERE WOUNDED.
29-YEAR-OLD JAMES DIGS WAS
TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL WHERE
HE LATER DIED FROM HIS
INJURIES.
THE OTHER TWO VICTIMS ARE
EXPECTED TO BE OKAY.
POLICE ARE CALLING THIS AN
ACTIVE INVESTIGATION.
NEW DETAILS IN THE DEADLY
HELICOPTER CRASH IN THE
BAHAMA THAT IS KILLED WEST
VIRGINIA BILLIONAIRE CHRIS
KLEIN.
WE'RE LEARNING MULTIPLE
AGENCIES ARE TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT WENT WRONG
INCLUDING THE NTSB AND THE
MANUFACTURER OF THE
HELICOPTER.
>> BECAUSE THE WRECKAGE WAS
FOUND IN SHALLOW WATER,
INVESTIGATORS SHOULD HAVE A
PRETTY GOOD IDEA OF WHAT
WENT WRONG.
>> Anchor: ACCORDING TO
AUTHORITIES THE CHOPPER WAS
ON ITS WAY TO FORT LAUDER
DALE WHEN IT WENT DOWN
BUT IT WASN'T REPORTED FOR
MORE THAN 12 HOURS, SIX
OTHERS INCLUDING KLEIN'S
DAUGHTER DIED IN THE CRASH.
TURNING BACK TO WEATHER LOOK
AT THIS VIDEO SENT TO US
FROM A VIEWER.
SEE JUST HOW STRONG THOSE
WINDS WERE AND HOW HARD THE
RAIN WAS FALLING IN THE
DISTRICT.
THIS WAS TAKEN AT THE WHARF
MENT.
PEOPLE FORCED TO TRY TO GET
TO SAFETY AS SOON AS
POSSIBLE T. FELT LIKE IT WAS
A FAST MOVER.
>> Reporter: IT ROCKED
THROUGH.
IT CAME THROUGH ROSLYN HERE.
I WAS DOING A Facebook
LIVE AND THE LIGHTNING HAD
ME JUMPING.
>> WE'VE BEEN SITTING HERE
SEEING IT.
>> Reporter: DOWN OVER
SOUTHERN MARYLAND BUT YOU
CAN SEE FLAPS IN THE
DISTANCE.
HOUR OR TWO FOR THE FOLKS
DOWN THERE AND GET A BREAK.
TOMORROW MORE SHOWERS.
TOMORROW'S RISK IS MORE
HEAVY DOWNPOURS, BUT WE
COULD HAVE ONE MORE ACTIVE
NIGHT.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE HEAT.
>> HUMIDITY LINGERS ONE MORE
DAY.
THIS IS TIME LAPSE PUT
TOGETHER EARLIER.
YOU CAN SEE GRAY SKIES.
IT GETS DARK.
WHEEL LIGHTS BACK UP AGAIN
AND THE SUNSHINE TRIES TO
PEER OUT AFTER THE FIRST
BAND OF HEAVY RAIN MOVES
THROUGH.
TALK ABOUT THE 90 DEGREE
DEGREES IF YOU LOOK BACK
OVER THE LAST COUPLE OF DAYS
WE'VE HAD FIVE.
90, 91, 92, 94.
MONDAY WAS OUR REPRIEVE.
WE HAD A SIX-DAY HEAT WAVE
AND ONE DAY OFF AND A FIVE-
DAY HEAT WAVE.
NOW MOVING FORWARD NOT GOING
TO PROMISE IT'S GOING TO
FEEL GREAT.
STILL GOING TO BE MUGGY BUT
TOMORROW WE DROP BELOW OUR
AVERAGE WHICH IS 88.
I THINK WE'LL BE IN THE UP
PER 80s, YOU WILL FEEL
MOISTURE IN THE AIR.
BY MONDAY MIDDLE 80'S MONDAY
UNSETTLED.
CLOUDS, SHOWERS, A COOLER
DAMPISH DAY.
IT WILL BRING IN DRYER AIR,
BUT MONDAY WE CLEAR OUT.
TUESDAY AND WEDNESDAY, LOOK
ING DELIGHTFUL.
PLENTY OF 70s OUT THERE.
SOUTH OF TOWN 80 FROM
QUANTICO, 83 FREDERICKSBURG
BUT THIS IS THE NUMBER YOU
HAVE TO PAY TAXI.
EVERY DEW POINT TEMPERATURE
OUT THERE IN THE 70s.
WHEN WE SEE DEW POINT
TEMPERATURES IN THE 0'S, IT
MEANS IT'S STICKY, SOUPY.
AWFUL.
BEST WAY TO DESCRIBE IT.
DOESN'T FEEL THAT GREAT OUT
THERE.
HERE IS GOOD NEWS, TOMORROW
SOUPY DAY FOR SUNDAY.
NOT AS HOT BUT SOUPY.
MONDAY WE TRANSITION,
FEELING STICKINESS BUT
TUESDAY, WEDNESDAY WE GET A
LULL THERE.
FEEL BETTER TUESDAY,
WEDNESDAY BEFORE WE CRANK IT
BACK UP AGAIN LATER IN THE
WEEK.
POINT LAST CLUSTER OF HEST
IER SHOWERS THROUGH
PORTIONS OF NORTHERN ST.
MARY'S COUNTY, OVER TO
MILLSTOWN, ALENS FRESH,
MECHANICSVILLE, HESTIER
POCKETS OF RAIN AND
LIGHTNING AS WELL.
LATER TONIGHT MOST OF THIS
FIZZLES.
MUGGY AND MILD TOMORROW
MORNING, MID DAY SHOWER OR
TWO BUT TOMORROW IN THE
EVENING MORE SHOWERS AND
STORMS AND THE BIGGER THREAT
COULD BE HEAVY POCKETS OF
RAIN.
8:00 HEAVY RAIN.
11:00, 12:00 TOMORROW NIGHT
HEAVY RAIN.
EVEN INTO MONDAY A
NORTHEASTERLY WIND AND
POCKETS OF RAIN.
WE MAY BE HARD-PRESSED TO
GET OUT OF THE LOW 80s
MONDAY.
I'M HOPEFUL BY MONDAY
EVENING WE'LL SEE CLEARING
AND DRYING BUT TOMORROW
STARTING OFF WITH SUNSHINE.
MUGGY, MID 80s FEELING
MORE LIKED 90s TOMORROW
BECAUSE OF THE HUMIDITY.
AT LEAST THE TEMPERATURE
WILL BE A FEW DEGREES LESS
AND MEASURE MONDAY, MONDAY
COULDING A WETTISH DAY.
TUESDAY, WEDNESDAY, SOLID.
NURSE A STORM OR TWO.
NO EXTREME HEAT BUT HUMIDITY
TAKES ANOTHER ABOUT 36 HOURS
BEFORE IT'S OUT.
>> I'M GLAD THERE ARE FEWER
SCORCHERS ON THE FORECAST.
LAST WEEK SO HOT.
IT'S TIME TO GRAB THE CUP.
>> ALL EYES IN FRANCE
TOMORROW, BIG GAMES FOR THE
U.S. WOMEN AS THEY TAKE ON
THE NETHERLANDS IN THE WORLD
CUP FINAL.
PLUS NEW UNIFORM, SAME
RESULT.
MAXIMUM SCHERZER DOMINANT
AGAIN TODAY FOR THE NATS.
SPORTS IS NEXT.
>> Announcer: NOW THE
TOYOTA SPORTS DESK.
>>ED WASHINGTON NATIONAL RE
PLACING THE WITH YOURY W.
WITH THE EXPOS N FOR ONE
DAY.
THIS AFTERNOON AT NATS PARK
THE TEAM HONORED THEIR PAST
CELEBRATING 50 YEARS SINCE
THE MONTREAL EXPOS JOINED
MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL.
NATS GET THINGS GOING EARLY
UP 1-0 IN THE SECT.
SUZUKI WITH A MAN ON, THE
BASEBALLS IS GONE.
3-0 WASHINGTON.
THEN NEW DADDY AGAIN MAX
SCHERZER TOOK OVER.
MAX WITH 11 STRIKEOUTS.
HE STOLE A BASE.
THE SECOND TIME IN HIS
CAREER HE STRIKE-OUT TEN
WITH A STOLEN BASE, ONLY TWO
OTHER PITCHERS HAVE DONE
THAT.
BOB GIBSON AND NOLAN RYAN.
THE NATS BACK IN THE WIN
COLUMN BEATING THE ROYAL 6-0
LETS SAY THE WASHINGTON WIZ
ARDS HAVE BEEN BUZZY THIS
OFF SEASON.
EARLIER TODAY THE TEAM
REPORTEDLY MAKING A MOVE TO
ACQUIRE SPURS FORWARD DAVIS
BERT TRAN ON THE HEELS OF
LAST NIGHT'S TRADE OF DWIGHT
HOWARD TO THE GRIZZLY.
IN RETURN THE WIZARDS GET C.
J.MYLES.
HE AVERAGED 9 POINTS AND 22
MINUTES FER GAME FOR THE
GRIZ LIST.
THIS IS THE LATEST MOVE THAT
POINTS TO WASHINGTON UNDERGO
ING A BIG MAKEOVER,
ONE THAT COULD SIGNAL A
FRANCHISE REBUILD.
LEONARD WANTED TO PLAY WITH
ANOTHER STAR AFTERALL.
JUST TURNS OUT THE PLAYER
WAS NOT LEBRON JAMES.
LEONARD AND PAUL GEORGE ARE
JOINING THE L.A.CLIPPERS, A
SHOCKNER A WILD NBA AGENCY.
TRADING FOR GEORGE DIDN'T
COME OPEN.
THE CLIPPER SENT OKLAHOMA
CITY FOUR UNPROTECTED FIRST
ROUND PICK AND SHEA
ALEXANDER AND GALINARI.
THE WIZARDS' FIRST TASTE OF
THE SUMMER LEAGUE TAKING ON
THE ZIONLESS PELICANS.
ROB INSON TAKING THE
CONTACTS.
GETS THE BASKET.
14 POINTS FOR THE ROOKIE.
LATER FIRST ROUND PICK, LOOK
AT THE BLOCK, RUI WITH A MOD
EST 4 POINTS AS THE WIZ
ARDS LEAD NEW ORLEANS
RIGHT NOW 65-52 IN THE THIRD
QUARTER.
ONE GAME FOR THE
CHAMPIONSHIP.
THE U.S. WOMEN'S NATIONAL
SOCCER TEAM ON THE VERGE OF
GOING BACK-TO-BACK.
THE AMERICANS WILL BATTLE
THE NETHERLANDS FOR THAT BIG
GOAL TROPHY.
TEAM USA WENT THROUGH A VERY
DIFFICULT ROAD TO GET TO THE
FINAL BEATING SPAIN, FRANCE
AND ENGLAND DURING THE KNOCK
OUT STAGE.
THE PLAYERS HAVE EVERY
REASON TO BE CONFIDENT BUT
THEY KNOW IT WILL TAKE THEIR
BEST EFFORT TO GET PAST THE
DUTCH.
>> THEY MOVE THE BALL VERY
WELL AND VERY DISCIPLINED IN
WHAT THEY DO.
I EXPECT IT TO BE A VERY
COMPETITIVE MATCH.
>> CHAMPIONS OF EUROPE,
WE'VE SEEN FIRST HAND WHAT
IT'S LIKE TO GO THROUGH
EUROPE LIKE THAT.
VERY DIFFICULT.
QUALITY IS SO HIGH AND FOR
THEM TO BE CHAMPIONS OF
EUROPE AND HAVE THAT
PEDESTRIAN DEGREE AND
EXPERIENCE -- PEDIGREE AND
EXPERIENCE THEY'RE A GREAT
TEAM.
>> Reporter:  TOMORROW'S
FINAL WILL START AT 11:00
A.M.
THE WASHINGTON SPIRIT ON THE
ROAD TONIGHT BATTLING
ORLANDO CITY.
30th MINUTE THE GREAT FEED
TO MANAGEMENTUS, THAT IS THE
GOAL THE SPIRIT TIE THE GAME
AT 2 BUT ORLANDO TAKING THE
CAME LITERALLY OFF OF A
WASHINGTON TURNOVER.
MARTA FINISHES IN STYLE.
BAD LOSS FOR THE SPIRIT LOS
ING TO ORLANDO 4-3.
ALSO SUR ARENA WILLIAMS MOV
ING TO THE SECOND WEEK AT
WOMEN BILL DON BEATING GERG
U.S., 6, 3, 6-4.
THE 16th TIME SHE HAS
REACHED THE ROUND OF 16.
CARL, WILLIAM IS PRETTY --
>> AMAZING, I CAN'T WENT TO
SEE COCO.
MONDAY, 10:00 A.M.
>> COME UP AT 11:00 IT START
ED AS A DOGGY DAYCARE
BUT WHEN THE OWNER FOUND OUT
THEY HAD
>> Anchor: NEW VIDEO FROM
SPACE X. SHOWS A PIECE OF
ONE OF ITS ROCKETS AS IT
PLUMMETED BACK TO EARTH LAST
MONTH.
THIS IS ESPECIALLY IMPORTANT
FOR THE COMPANY BECAUSE THIS
WAS THE FIRST TIME AFTER A
LAUNCH IS SUCCESSFULLY
RECOVERED A PIECE OF THE
ROCKET'S NOSE CONE.
IT'S AN IMPORTANT STEP
TOWARDS THEIR GOAL OF REUS
ING HARDWARE TO DRIVE
DOWN THE COST OF LAUNCHES.
PUPS, A NEBRASKA COUPLE IS
USING BOTH AS INGREDIENTS IN
THEIR NEWEST BUSINESS VENT
URE.
IT'S NEBRASKA FIRST DOG BAR.
AT FIRST THE BUSINESS WAS A
DOGGY DAYCARE BUT THEY HAD
EXTRA SPACE SO THEY DECIDED
TO GET A LIQUOR LICENSE AND
SERVE DRINKS TO THE OWNERS
WHILE THE PUPS PLAY.
BRIAN HAS A FINAL CHECK