WEEK LATE.
ABC7 BREAKING DOWN THE STORY.
>> THIS GOES BEYOND HIS
INFAMOUS PHOTO AND TONIGHT'S
SCHOOL PLAN TO MAKE UP FOR IT
FOLLOWING THE APOLOGY.
>> A D.C. DRAG QUEEN PLAN
HATCHED ON HIS GOVERNMENT
COMPUTER.
>> WE ARE THREE HOURS AWAY
FROM THE "STATE OF THE UNION."
>> THE PRESIDENT UNINVITED TO
DELIVER AT IT WEEK AGO AFTER
THE SHUTDOWN.
SCOTT SCOTT JOINS US LIVE
ON -- SCOTT THUMAN JOINS US
LIVE ON THE HILL.
WHAT DO WE EXPECT TO HEAR
TONIGHT?
>> Scott: HE KNOWS WITH THE
DEMOCRATS IN POWER IN HOUSE HE
HAS TO GET SOME OF THEM ON
BOARD IF HE IS GOING TO PASS
LEGISLATION.
HE KNOWS THE IDEA OF SELLING
OPTIMISM CAN BE TOUGH.
ESPECIALLY CONSIDERING THE
ENVIRONMENT HERE.
>> WHEN PRESIDENT TRUMP TAKES
CENTER STAGE TUESDAY NIGHT HE
WILL CALL FOR UNITY AND THE
BIPARTISANSHIP.
LATEST IMMIGRATION FIGHT PROOF
THERE HAS BEEN LITTLE TO GO
AROUND LATELY.
>> HE WANTS LESS DIVISIVENESS.
>> COMMON GROUND COULD BE
FOUND OVER LOWERING
PRESCRIPTION DRUG COSTS OR
APPROVING SHOVEL-READY PROJECT
FOR THE AGING INFRASTRUCTURE.
>> HE MADE ALMOST IDENTICAL
STATEMENTS LAST YEAR AND THE
PROGRESS HAS BEEN PAINFULLY
SMALL.
>> HE WILL HAVE THE WORK CUT
OUT FOR HIM.
SKEPTICAL DEMOCRATS HOLD POWER
IN THE HOUSE.
AFTER ENDURING 35-DAY
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN THE THIRD
OF THE PRESIDENCY, HE IS TEN
DAYS FROM A POSSIBLE FOURTH.
>> HE HAS SHOWN HE IS GOOD AT
DIVIDING.
IT IS TIME TO DEMONSTRATE HE
IS GOOD AT UNITING.
>> THERE TRADE TO THE TROOP
MOVEMENT AND THE ULTIMATE
CONTROVERSY, THE WALL, HEALING
THE WOUNDS AND COALESCING WITH
THE CONGRESS COULD BE HIS
GREATEST CHALLENGE OR GREATEST
VICTORY SO FAR.
>> MY POLLING.
I SEE IT AS I TRAVEL THE
COUNTRY.
THEY WANT TO SEE BOTH PARTIES
WORK TOGETHER.
>> I SPOKE TO A LONG-TIME
DEMOCRATIC CONGRESSMAN.
I SAID ARE THERE ANY MEMBERS
ON THE LEFT THAT THE PRESIDENT
CAN WIN OVER TONIGHT?
HE SAID NO.
THAT IT IS NOT AN OPTION.
IF THEY BELIEVE IT IS
BENEFITING BOTH OF THEM AND
GETTING A FAIR SHAKE THEY WILL
WORK WITH THE WHITE HOUSE BUT
TO GET ANYONE TO CROSS THE
AISLE IS DIFFICULT TONIGHT.
REPORTING LIVE, STATUTORY
HALL, BACK TO YOU.
>> Nancy: THANK YOU.
SOME ROADS AROUND THE CAPITOL
ARE CLOSED TO THE PEDESTRIANS
AT THIS HOUR.
>> THE ONES IN RED WILL CLOSE
IN AN HOUR AT 7:00.
MOST OF THE PEOPLE ATTENDING
THE SPEECH WILL BE AT THE
CAPITOL ONCE THE ROADS CLOSE.
THAT IS THE FIRST PERSON
RELEASEDLEASED FROM PRISON AS A
RESULT OF THE FIRST STEP
PRISON REFORM BILL.
>> I'M GRATEFUL.
NOTHING I COULD HAVE IMAGINED
AND I'M THANKFUL.
>> IT ALSO INCLUDES THE FATHER
OF A SAILOR KILLED IN THE
ATTACK ON THE USS COLE.
>> WE WILL BRING YOU THE
COMPLETE STATE OF THE UNION
AND THE DEMOCRATIC RESPONSE AT
9:00 ON ABC7 AND THE SISTER
STATION WJLA 24/7 NEWS.
THEN THE COVERAGE WILL
CONTINUE ON ABC7 NEWS AT
11:00.
IN OTHER NEWS, AN APOLOGY FROM
THE PRESIDENT OF THE MEDICAL
SCHOOL THAT THE GOVERNOR
ATTENDED AFTER THE RACIST
PHOTOS SURFACED FROM ONE OF
THE SCHOOL'S YEARBOOKS.
>> Nancy: BUT DESPITE
INTENSE POLITICAL PRESSURE
THERE IS NO INDICATION THAT
RALPH NORTHAM PLANS TO STEP
DOWN.
MICHELLE MARSH BEGINS OUR TEAM
COVERAGE FROM RICHMOND.
>> Michelle: IN FACT, THE
PROTESTS DIED DOWN ON THE
SURFACE.
ON THE SURFACE IT APPEARED TO
BE BUSINESS AS USUAL.
THEY HAVE THE ALL-IMPORTANT
CROSSOVER DAY.
WE SAW THE LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR
JUSTIN FAIRFAX PRESIDING OVER
THE SENATE AS HE NORMALLY
DOES.
THIS IS AFTER ALLEGATIONS OF
SEXUAL ASSAULT RESURFACED
AGAINST HIM.
HE ADMITS TO THE ENCOUNTER HE
DENIES THAT HE SEXUALLY
ASSAULTED ANYONE.
GOVERNOR NORTHAM MEAN TIME
STILL UNDER PRESSURE TO RESIGN
AFTER THE DILLS COVERRY OF THE
RACE -- DISCOVERY OF THE
RACIST YEARBOOK PHOTO ON HIS
PAGE FROM 1984.
>> I CANNOT TELL YOU WHY HE
HASN'T RESIGNED BUT I'M
PRAYING HE WOULD DO THAT AND
GET IT BEHIND US.
>> YOU ARE STILL ABLE TO GET
AHEAD WITH THE LEGISLATIVE
AGENDA WITHOUT ANY OF THE
CONTROVERSIES SURROUNDING THE
GOVERNOR NOR THE LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR AFFECTING BUSINESS?
>> WE HAVE WORKED ON THE
FLOOR.
WE HAVE HAD DEBATE ON THE
LEGISLATION.
WE TALKED ABOUT THE THINGS
THAT MATTER AND WE ARE
CONTINUING TO MOVE FORWARD.
>> WHEN IT COMES TO THE RACIST
IMAGE THAT APPEARED ON
NORTHAM'S YEARBOOK PAGE THE
UNIVERSITY EASTERN MEDICAL
VIRGINIA -- EASTERN VIRGINIA
MEDICAL SCHOOL TAKES FULL
RESPONSIBILITY FOR THAT.
TIM BARBER WAS THERE WHEN THE
SCHOOL ADDRESSED THE ISSUE.
IS THERE WE ARE SERIOUS ABOUT
FINDING THE FACTS OF WHAT
HAPPENED.
>> FOUR DAYS AFTER THE PHOTO
OF GOVERNOR NORTHAM'S 1984
YEARBOOK PAGE RESURFACED THE
PROVOST OF THE GOVERNOR'S ALMA
MATTER EASTERN VIRGINIA
MEDICAL SCHOOL IS LAUNCHING AN
INVESTIGATION IN TO WHY PHOTOS
LIKE THIS WERE ALLOWED.
>> SOME ARE REPUGNANT AND
UNPROFESSIONAL AND SOME ARE
ABHORRENT.
>> THE INVESTIGATION IS RUN BY
THE FORMER ATTORNEY GENERAL
COHEN WHO IS REPRESENTING THE
VICE PRESIDENT IN THE MUELLER
RUSSIA PROBE.
HE WILL LOOK AT THE OTHER
PICTURES SUCH AS THE STUDENTS
IN CONFEDERATE UNIFORMS FROM
2014.
PICTURES THAT PROMPTED THE
PROVOST TO PUT AN END TO
YEARBOOK PRODUCTION.
GOVERNOR NORTHAM FIRST SAID HE
WAS IN THE PHOTO AND THEN
DENIED IT AND THEN ADMITTED TO
WEARING BLACKFACE IN A DANCE
COMPETITION.
>> I BELIEVE YOU DESERVE TO
HEAR FROM ME.
>> HE DEMANDS TIME TO PROVE
HIS PAST THE MEDICAL SCHOOL
THAT GAVE THE GOVERNOR HIS
START IS EXAMINING ITS OWN.
>> TIM BARBER, ABC7 NEWS.
>> WHILE THE GOVERNOR MAY TRY
TO WIN OVER THOSE WHO WANT HIM
OUT OF OFFICE THROUGH TIME, WE
GAINING THE TRUST, ONE
LAWMAKER SENATOR LUCAS SAYS HE
NEEDS TO RESIGN NOW.
TIME WON'T MAKE THE ISSUE
BETTER.
WE WANT TO URGE YOU TO STAY
WITH US FOR THE CONTINUING
COVERAGE ON RICHMOND AND
WATCHING FOR ALL DEVELOPMENTS
FROM THE GOVERNOR'S MANSION.
DOWNLOAD THE FREE NEWS APP TO
GET PUSH ALERTS OR UPDATES
WITH A NEW DEVELOPMENT.
THAT IS THE LATEST.
I'M MICHELLE MARSH.
BACK TO YOU.
>> Jonathan: THANK YOU.
A POSSIBLE TRANSFORMER
EXPLODED AND RAT 9 -- RATTLED
A LOT OF NERVES.
THIS LED UP TO THE KEY BRIDGE
A MAJOR ARTERY.
THE ROADS ARE BACK OWN
TONIGHT.
NOBODY HAS BEEN HURT.
SO THAT IS GOOD.
>> OUTPOURING OF SUPPORT IN
THE LAST HOUR AFTER THE FIVE
CHILDREN WERE KILLED IN A
HORRIFIC CRASH.
>> TWO LOCAL MEN ARRESTED IN
MIAMI FOR ALLEGEDLY TRYING TO
SNEAK A VAST AMOUNT OF DRUGS
ONTO A CRUISE SHIP.
THE STORY IN A MOMENT.
>> GOOD EVENING.
I'M CHIEF METEOROLOGIST BILL
KELLY.
NOWHERE HALL HIGH IN
MID-40s.
IN THE 6:00 HOUR WE ARE STILL
KNOCKING ON THE DOOR OF 70.
A RECORD-BREAKING DAY.
I MAY NOT BE THE ONLY ONE THIS
WEEK.
WE WILL TALK ABOUT THAT IN
MINUTES.
>> Nancy: TONIGHT TEN PEOPLE
DEAD AFTER THE MASSIVE FIRE
TORE THROUGH APARTMENT COMPLEX
IN PARIS.
SOME RESIDENTS THERE CLIMBING
TO THE ROOF OF THE NINE-STORY
BUILDING JUST TO TRY TO
ESCAPE.
A 40-YEAR-OLD WOMAN WHO LIVED
IN THE BUILDING UNDER ARREST
TONIGHT.
POLICE SAY SHE HAS A HISTORY
OF MENTAL PROBLEMS.
>> Jonathan: WE ARE GETTING
NEW INFORMATION AFTER A DEADLY
PLANE CRASH IN PENNSYLVANIA.
THE PILOT MAY NOT HAVE BEEN
WHO HE CLAIMED TO BE.
INITIAL REPORTS HE WAS A
RETIRED POLICE OFFICER FROM
CHICAGO LIVEING IN NEVADA.
BUT TODAY THEY CAME OUT AND
SAID THERE IS NO RECORD HE WAS
EVER WITH THE FORCE.
THEY ARE TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHY THE TWIN ENGINE PLANE
BROKE APART OVER NEIGHBORHOOD
KILLING A PILOT AND FOUR
PEOPLE IN A HOME CELEBRATING
THE SUPER BOWL.
ONLY ON 7, TWO MEN ACCUSED OF
STEALING $500,000 OF COPPER
FROM CONSTRUCTION SITE, PIPES
WERE TAKEN IN WHITE OAK.
WHERE THE NEW WASHINGTON
AVENTIS HOSPITAL WILL BE
BUILT.
THEY BROKE IN A FENCED OFF
WORK AREA TEN TIMES OVER A
NINE- . MONTH PERIOD.
THEY WERE CAUGHT AFTER THE
POLICE CONNECTED THEM TO CRIME
SCENE USING THE G.P.S.
INFORMATION FROM THE CELL
PHONES.
>> Nancy: COMING UP AT
6:00 --
>> EXAMPLE OF HOW THE COAST
GUARD DELIVERS MISSION
EXCELLENCE ANYTIME, ANYWHERE.
>> Nancy: EVEN WHEN THEY ARE
NOT PAID.
THE COAST GUARD IMPRESSIVE
WORK IN THE PARTIAL GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN.
>> Jonathan: LESS THAN 24
HOURS AFTER "7 ON YOUR SIDE"
BROUGHT YOU STARTLING NEWS
ABOUT INSULIN PRICES A LOCAL
LAWMAKER SAYS HE WANTS TO FIND
OUT WHY THE DRUG COSTS SO
MUCH.
>> Nancy: BACK NOW AT 6:15.
LOOK AT THIS.
THE U.S. COAST GUARD
OFFLOADING 35,000 POUNDS OF
COCAINE.
THIS WAS IN FLORIDA.
THOSE WERE ALL THE DRUGS
INTERCEPTED IN SHUTDOWN WHEN
THE AGENTS WERE NOT BEING
PAID.
THIS AS TWO D.C. MEN ACCUSE OF
TRYING TO SMUGGLE DRUGS ON A
CRUISE SHIP IN MIAMI.
ONE WORKED AT THE PENTAGON.
>> FUN-LOVING GUYS.
ONE OF THE MEN CHARGED PETER
MELENDEZ MADE A SPLASH IN THE
DRAG SEW SEEN ON YouTube
MISS ADAMS MORGAN.
MELENDEZ WON THE CROWN IN
2015.
THE 35-YEAR-OLD AND HIS PAL
AND ROOMMATE 27-YEAR-OLD
ROBERT KOEHLER NOT LOOKING
VERY HAPPY AFTER THE BUST FOR
ALLEGEDLY BOARDING A GAY PARTY
SHIP WITH A BOATLOAD OF DRUGS
INTENDING TO DISBURSE IT TO
FELLOW PASSENGERS.
THE FORMER PASSENGER BILL
THOMPSON ISN'T SURPRISED.
>> I DON'T DO DRUGS SO I CAN'T
SPEAK FIRST-HAND.
BUT IF THERE WILL 3,000, 4,000
PEOPLE ON A BOAT NO MATTER
WHAT KIND OF A CRUISE IT IS,
THERE ARE A LOT OF THINGS
GOING ON.
>> MELENDEZ A CRANK TO OR
APPARENTLY USED THE WORK
COMPUTER PLANNING THE
OPERATION.
INVESTIGATOR FROM HOMELAND
SECURITY UNEARTHED THE PLANS
AND TIPPED OFF AUTHORITIES IN
MIAMI.
FRIEND AND ACQUAINTANCES OF
MELENDEZ TELL US ASIDE FROM
HIS GOVERNMENT JOB HE WORKED
WEEKENDS AS A GO-GO DANCER AT
PRIVATE PARTIES.
THEY MAINTAIN THE TWO MEN HAD
A LARGE QUANTITY OF PARTY
DRUGS, "K" AND GHB CALLED "G."
WITH MOLLY, VIAGRA AND
ADDERALL.
>> IT'S LIKE GOING TO A BAR
AND HAVING DRINKS.
IT'S GOING TO A PARTY, YOU
KNOW, HAVING SOME RECREATIONAL
DRUGS.
>> WE WENT TO THE MEN'S HOME
IN D.C.
THEY ARE BACK BUT NOT IN THE
MOOD TO TALK ABOUT THE WINTER
BREAK THAT COULD PUT THEM
BEHIND BARS.
STEPHEN TSCHIDA, ABC7 NEWS.
>> Nancy: NOW TO AN
EMOTIONAL CANDLELIGHT VIGIL
WRAPPING UP IN PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY FOR FIVE CHILDREN
KILLED IN A WEEKEND CAR CRASH.
>> Jonathan: MORE THAN 75
PEOPLE GATHERING OUTSIDE THE
MORNING SIDE TOWN HALL.
SHARING HUGS AND PRAYERS AND
STORIES ABOUT THE CHILDREN
AGING 5, 6, 8,14 AND 15.
EMOTIONS ON DISPLAY AS THAW
PREPARED TO RELEASE BALLOONS.
>> JUST TOOK A PIECE OF MY
HEART.
I WANT TO HE HER I LOVE HER.
>> MARYLAND STATE POLICE STILL
INVESTIGATING THE CAUSE OF THE
CRASH AS WELL AS ALL FIVE
CHILDREN WERE NOT WEARING SEAT
BELTS.
THE MOTHER OF TWO OF THE
CHILDREN WAS BEHIND THE WHEEL
AT THE TIME OF THE CRASH.
SHE HAS BEEN RELEASED FROM THE
HOSPITAL.
>> Nancy: NEW HOPE FIGHTING
THE OPIOID CRISIS IN AMERICA
TODAY.
DOZENS OF PEOPLE TURNING OUT
FOR THE RIBBON CUTTING AT
BROOK'S HOUSE.
TREATMENT CENTER FOUNDED BY A
FORMER NARCOTICS OFFICER WHO
LOST HIS FATHER TO -- LOST HIS
DAUGHTER TO ADDICTION.
WE INTRODUCED YOU TO HIM THREE
YEARS AGO AND HE HOPES THE
FACILITY IN HAGERSTOWN HELPS
OTHERS GET THE TREATMENT THEY
NEED.
>> UPDATING TONIGHT ON THE
FIGHT TO MAKE LIFE SAVING DRUG
MORE AFFORDABLE.
LAST NIGHT AT 6:00, WE SHOWED
YOU HOW INSULIN PRICES WERE
SKYROCKETING ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
THIS AFTERNOON, TIM KAINE
CALLED ON THE DRUG COMPANIES
TO EXPLAIN WHY.
HE IS ASKING FOR MORE
INFORMATION FROM ELI LILY, AND
OTHERS TO TRY TO BRING PRICES
DOWN.
>> Nancy: A PLAN FOR THE
PEDESTRIAN SAFETY RAISING RED
FLAGS NOW ABOUT THE TRAFFIC
AND GRIDLOCK.
STARTING IN JULY, YOU WON'T BE
ABLE TO TURN RIGHT ON RED AT
HUNDREDS OF INTERSECTIONS IN
D.C.
CHANGES WILL BE AROUND THE
HIGH SCHOOLS AND THE AREAS
WITH THE PLENTY OF THE
PEDESTRIANS AND THE CYCLISTS
TO CUT DOWN ON CRASHES WITH
THEM.
BUT STATS FROM THE D.C. POLICE
SHOW THAT OF THE MORE THAN
107,000 CRASHES IN THE CITY,
BETWEEN 2013 AND 2015, TURNING
RIGHT ON RED WAS ONLY FACTOR
IN 55 OF THEM.
>> Jonathan: 7 ON STORM
WATCH WITH THE DRASTIC CHANGES
IN THE WEATHER ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
WE BROKE A RECORD AROUND HERE
WITH TEMPERATURES REACHING 72
AT REAGAN NATIONAL AIRPORT.
>> Bill: 74.
>> Jonathan: UPDATE.
CHIEF METEOROLOGIST SAYS 74.
THIS IS DAYS AFTER MAKING IT
OUT OF THE 20S BARELY.
BUT OUT WEST A MASSIVE SNOW --
STORM DUMPING SNOW IN OREGON
TO THE ISIERRA.
THEY HAD NINE FEET OF SNOW IN
24-HOUR PERIOD AND IT SHUT
DOWN THE SKI RESORTS AROUND
THE AREA BECAUSE IT'S NOT
SAFE.
AVALANCHE, DEAL WITH THAT.
IT'S NINE FEET OF SNOW.
>> Bill: NOT A SMALL AMOUNT.
GOOD AMOUNT FOR A SEASON, LET
ALONE FOR 40 HOURS.
FOR US --
>> Nancy: IT WAS NICE.
I WENT RUNNING IN SHORTS AND
EVERYTHING.
>> Bill: I NEED THE SUN TO
SET LATER SO I CAN TAKE A BIKE
RIDE.
TEMPERATURES YOU COULD WITH
70s AROUND THE AREA.
WE ARE STILL AT 67 DEGREES NOW
IN D.C.
YOU HAVE 62 AT CHANTILLY.
62 IN MARTINSBURG.
THE TEMPERATURES, THE ALMANAC.
YOU HAVE DON'T RUN THIS UNLESS
IT'S SOMETHING OF THE
SIGNIFICANT BECAUSE WE HAVE
PASSED THIS TIME OF THE DAY.
74 DEGREES IS THE HIGH TODAY.
THE RECORD WAS 70.
WHEN WE LOOK AT THE 74, IT IS
THE WARMEST, THE EARLIEST
74-DEGREE TEMPERATURE WE HAVE
HAD SINCE 2002.
WHEN WE HAD 77 IN JANUARY.
RECORD SHATTERING DAY.
WE BROKE IT BY FOUR DEGREES.
IMPRESSIVE.
I HOPE YOU GOT OUT TO ENJOY.
A FEW CLOUDS WORKING IN THE
AREA NOW.
WE ARE QUIET.
WE WILL LOOK AT THE FUTURE
CAST WITH THE TEMPERATURES ON
IT.
THE TEMPERATURES PLAY A BIG
ROLE IN THE STORY.
SO BY 1:00.
OVERNIGHT AND MIDNIGHT WE ARE
STILL IN THE MID-TO-UPPER
40s.
OUT THE DOOR.
7:00, 8:00 9:00.
MID-40s.
DRY FOR MORNING DRIVE.
BUT GOING THROUGH THE DAY THE
NUMBERS WON'T MOVE MUCH.
IT'S ABOVE NORMAL AND COOLER
THAN TODAY.
FOR SURE.
TEMPERATURES BY 12:00 NOON IN
THE UPPER 40s TO 50.
THAT IS ESSENTIALLY WHERE WE
STAY.
THE NEXT WEATHER MAKER IN
TOMORROW.
AT THIS TIME TOMORROW NIGHT.
I WOULD EXPECT RAIN AROUND THE
AREA.
YOU WILL LIKELY HAVE TO USE
THE WINDSHIELD WIPERS FOR THE
DRIVE HOME.
BRING YOUR UMBRELLA WITH YOU.
YOU WON'T NEED IT IN THE
MORNING.
THE KIDS, SAME FOR THE BUS
STOP.
THEY WON'T NEED IT IN THE
MORNING BUT IN THE AFTERNOON
THEY MIGHT NEED THAT.
THEN THAT WILL SCOOT THROUGH.
WE WILL KEEP RAIN IN THE
FORECAST OFF AND ON OVERNIGHT
TO THURSDAY.
WE ARE LOOKING AT THE LOW
50s FOR THE DAY TOMORROW.
THAT IS THE HIGH.
THE RAIN IS COMING IN MAINLY
IN THE EVENING AND IT WILL GO
INTO THURSDAY MORNING.
PRAY MARELY THE FIRST --
PRIMARILY THE FIRST PART OF
THE DAY.
THURSDAY AFTERNOON AND THE
EVENING I EXPECT IT TO GET OUT
OF HERE.
I HAVE 64 ON THURSDAY.
A DAY.
I TWEETED THIS OUT.
IT'S REALLY GOING TO DEPEND
WHERE YOU LIVE.
WE HAVE THE POTENTIAL TO SEE A
MAJOR DIFFERENCE BETWEEN YOU
AND FREDERICKSBURG.
YOU FOLKS UP NEAR THE
BALTIMORE AREA.
BUT BY THIS WEEKEND IT WILL BE
BACK TO FEELING LIKE WINTER
WITH THE TEMPERATURES IN THE
30s.
>> Jonathan: GET OUT OF
HERE.
NECK BREAKING.
BILL, THANKS.
HEAD TO GEORGE WASHINGTON
UNIVERSITY WHERE WE FIND
ROBERT BURTON.
>> Nancy: HE IS ON HAND FOR
A CLINIC THAT IS AIMED AT
EMPOWERING YOUNG WOMEN.
ROBERT?
>> Robert: YEAH.
WE JUST GOT DONE, IN FACT,
CELEBRATING WOMEN.
BUT FIRST, JOHN WALL.
WE'LL GIVE YOU DETAILS ON WHY
HE MIGHT BE OUT FOR THE ENTIRE
NEXT SEASON.
COMING UP NEXT
>> Robert: WELCOME BACK.
WE ARE LIVE AT G.W. WHERE WE
JUST GOT DONE CELEBRATING
YOUNG WOMEN IN SPORTS.
BUT BEFORE THAT, DEVASTATING
NEWS FROM THE WIZARDS CAMP.
JOHN WALL, YES, HE WAS ALREADY
OUTS FOR THE REST OF THIS
SEASON BUT HE COULD BE OUT THE
FOLLOWING SEASON.
HERE IS WHY.
APPARENTLY HE WAS AT HIS HOUSE
AND HE SLIPPED AND ENDED UP
RUPTURING HIS ACHILLES.
HIS RECOVERY TIME PREDICTED TO
BE 11 TO 15 MONTHS.
HERE IS WHAT HURTS.
NEXT YEAR, HE SLATED TO MAKE
$37.8 MILLION.
FROM THEN ON, NOTHING LOWER
THAN $40 MILLION.
MASSIVE CONTRACT.
MOVING ON, THIS IS WHY WE ARE
HERE.
AWESOME DAY FOR G.W. AND THE
WOMEN'S SPORTS FOUNDATION.
THEY TEAMED UP TO TEACH YOUNG
GIRLS ABOUT HEALTH, FITNESS,
BODY IMAGE.
SO MANY ABLETIVITYS.
THE DAY BEFORE NATIONAL WOMEN
IN SPORTS DAY.
WE TALK ABOUT BASKETBALL,
SOFTBALL CLINICS, TENNIS AND
GYMNASTICS.
COLLEGE ATHLETES HELPING
COACHES.
WE SPOKE TO THE WOMEN'S SPORTS
FOUNDATION AND SHE SAYS THAT
EVENTS LIKE THIS ARE CRITICAL.
>> THREE IN FIVE GIRLS DON'T
HAVE ENOUGH PHYSICAL ACTIVITY.
SO THE MORE WE GET THEM
ACTIVE, THEY ARE HEALTHIER AND
THEY WILL LEARN WHAT SPORTS
HAVE GIVE LIKE LEADERSHIP,
CONFIDENCE BUILDING AND
POSITIVE BODY IMAGE.
THAT'S WHAT THE WOMEN'S SPORTS
FOUNDATION IS ABOUT.
>> Robert: HAD A LOT OF FUN
HEAR, GUYS.
MAYBE TOO MUCH FUN.
BACK TO YOU.
>> Jonathan: ALL RIGHT.
THANKS.
IT DOES LOOK LIKE A GOOD TIME.
>> Nancy: "WORLD NEWS
TONIGHT" WITH MAUER COMING
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
>> NOW ABC7 NEWS AT NOON.
ON YOUR SIDE.
>>Adrianna: AS A COME ON THE
AIR AT NOON.
RAIN IS STILL COMING DOWN
ENTERING THE START OF THE WORK
WEEK INTO A SLOPPY MESS.IT
WINTRY MIX THAT LEFT SNOW IN
SOME AREAS CAUSED SCHOOL DELAYS
THIS MORNING AND SOME CLOSURES.
THINGS ARE QUIETING DOWN BUT
STILL, THERE IS MORE RAIN TO
COME.
>>Steve: A LOT MORE RAIN ON THE
WAY TONIGHT INTO THE DAY
TOMORROW.
OUT NEAR DULLES INTERNATIONAL
AIRPORT AND LOOKING AT THE
WINTRY MIX AND WE DO HAVE A
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY NOW FOR
FREDERICK COUNTY AND WASHINGTON
COUNTY AND WESTERN MARYLAND.
THIS IS THROUGH THIS AFTERNOON
IN TWO TONIGHT AND THROUGH
EARLY TOMORROW MORNING.
A WINTER STORM WARNING FOR
GARRETT AND ALLEGHENY CAN ELSE.
YOUR ADVISORS FROM THE
IMMEDIATE METRO AREA.
A WALL WITHIN THE ACTION OF THE
NEXT-TO-LAST HOUR BUT NOW
FILLING IN WITH RAIN THROUGH
ARLINGTON OVER THROUGH TYSONS
BUT WE STILL HAVE A BIT OF THE
WINTRY MIX IT SNOW UP TO
FREDERICK AND WE ARE NOT
LOOKING AT ANY ADDITIONAL
COMMISSIONS TO THE NORTH, AT
LEAST NOT RIGHT NOW.
HERE IS TO THE BELTWAY IF YOU
ARE TRAVELING OVER THROUGH
ESTHER HARPER AREA AND LOOKING
AT WHAT ROADWAYS EMAIL TO SLOW
IT DOWN A BIT.
WITH MORE RAIN ON THE WAY WITH
THE EVENING RUSH HOUR COMMUTE.
TEMPERATURES ARE STILL WELL
ABOVE FREEZING AND 37 AT REAGAN
NATIONAL AIRPORT IN A LITTLE
BIT COLDER OFF TO THE WEST OF
US.
RIGHT AT THE FREEZING MARK FOR
WINCHESTER AND OVER INTO A.
HERE IS OUR HOURLY FORECAST IF
YOU ARE GRABBING A BITE FOR
LUNCH OR HAVE ANY OUTDOOR
ACTIVITIES PLAN.
MAKE SURE YOU HAVE AN UMBRELLA.
WE ARE NOT TALKING ABOUT HEAVY
RAIN BUT WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
POCKETS OF RAIN THAT WILL
CONTINUE TO THE AFTERNOON AND
INTO THE EVENING WITH
TEMPERATURES IN THE UPPER 30S.
TALKING ABOUT TONIGHT AND THE
POTENTIAL FOR SLICK SPOTS,
EARLY TOMORROW MORNING, BUT
THERE IS LIGHT AT THE END OF
THE TUNNEL.
WE HAVE MILDER TEMPERATURES ON
THE WAY IT WOULDN'T YOU KNOW
IT?
JUST IN TIME FOR VALENTINE'S
DAY.
MORE ON THAT IN A FEW MINUTES.
>>Adrianna: THANK YOU STEVE.
POLITICAL CHAOS CONTINUES TO
HAVE A HOLD ON THE
COMMONWEALTH.
THE BUSINESS OF STATE
GOVERNMENT CONTINUES.
AS POLITICAL FUTURES ARE STILL
UNCERTAIN, ALL EYES REMAIN ON
RICHMOND AND DOMICILES IS LIVE
FROM THE STATE CAPITAL WITH
THIS LATEST TWIST.
>>John: GOOD AFTERNOON AND TAKE
A LOOK AT THIS FRONT AND CENTER
ON THE RICHMOND TIMES DISPATCH
AND AT THIS HOUR, STATE
DELEGATES ARE FILING INTO THE
STATE CAPITAL HERE IN RICHMOND.
THE GENERAL ASSEMBLY WILL
CONVENE AT THIS HOUR, BUT THERE
WILL BE NO FILING FOR AN
IMPEACHMENT JUST YET.
>>> A SERIES OF SCANDALS
STARTED 10 DAYS AGO THAT SHOOK
THE STATE CAPITAL HERE IN
RICHMOND.
THE LATEST TREMOR HAS FIZZLED A
BIT, INITIALLY DEMOCRATIC
DELEGATE PATRICK HOPE SAID HE
WOULD BEGIN THE IMPEACHMENT
PROCESS AGAINST LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR JUSTIN FAIRFAX.
BUT NOW HOPE SAYS HE WANTS TO
WAIT IT OUT.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE, NOW, MORE
THAN ONE CREDIBLE ALLEGATION.
THE LAST ONE WHICH HAS BEEN
CORROBORATED AT THE TIME.
HE HAS TO RESIGN.
>> THE DELEGATE SAID HE
RECEIVED AN ENORMOUS AMOUNT OF
SINCERE AND THOUGHTFUL FEEDBACK
BUT ADDITIONAL COMPLETION IS
NEEDED TO TAKE PLACE BEFORE
ANYTHING IS FILED.
IN THE MEANTIME, JUSTIN FAIRFAX
IS URGING THE FBI TO LOOK INTO
THE BRIEF CLAIMS BY TWO
DIFFERENT WOMEN.
>> THEY COULD, IN THEORY, HAND
THE STATE WHICH HAD BEEN
TRENDING DEMOCRATIC BACK TO
REPUBLICANS FOR A LONG TIME.
>>John: THROUGH ATTORNEYS FOR
BOTH WOMEN, VANESSA TYSON AND
MEREDITH WATSON SAID THEY ARE
WILLING TO TESTIFY IF AN
IMPEACHMENT HEARING AND SO
MOVING FORWARD.
>> I BELIEVE BOTH WOMEN AND I
SEE NO REASON WHY PEOPLE COME
BEFORE BUT THERE'S NOTHING TO
GAIN, NO LAWSUIT OR MONEY
INVOLVED.
THESE WERE BOTH DOCUMENTS SOME
YEARS BACK IT WAS NOT CREATED
OVERNIGHT.
I BELIEVE THE WOMEN AND I THINK
IF YOU BELIEVE THE WOMEN THAT
WE HAVE NO CALL TO CALL FOR HIS
RESIGNATION.
>>John: DELICATE HOPE TO PUT
OUT AN OFFICIAL STATEMENT THIS
MORNING SAYING IN PART,
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR FAIRFAX
SHOULD HAVE ALREADY RESIGNED.
IT IS ATROCIOUS THAT HE WILL BE
PRESIDING OVER THE SENATE OF
VIRGINIA WITH THESE
ALLEGATIONS.
THE MESSAGE BEING SAID, HE
SAYS, TO THE VICTIM'S OF SEXUAL
ASSAULT IS CHILLING AND HE IS
RENEWING HIS CALL FOR FAIRFAX
TO RESIGN IMMEDIATELY.UT THE
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR VEHEMENTLY
DENIES ALL OF THE ALLEGATIONS.
REPORTING LIVE AT THE STATE
CAPITAL HERE IN RICHMOND, JOHN
GONZALEZ ABC7 NEWS.
>>Adrianna: ,RALPH NORTHAM
STRING OF MORE CONTROVERSY
DURING HIS FIRST TV INTERVIEW
SINCE ADMITTING TO INVITE FACE
AT A PARTY IN THE 80S BUT HE IS
NOW UNDER FIRE FOR HIS CHOICE
OF WORDS WHEN ADDRESSING THE
400 YEAR ANNIVERSARY OF THE
FIRST SLAVES BROUGHT TO
AMERICA.>> I KNOW THIS HAS
BEEN A VERY DIFFICULT WEEK FOR
YOU AND THE STATEOF VIRGINIA.
WHERE WOULD YOU LIKE TO BEGIN?
>> IT HAS BEEN A DIFFICULT WEEK
AND IF YOU LOOK AT VIRGINIA'S
HISTORY WE ARE NOW AT THE 400
YEAR ANNIVERSARY , JUST 90
MILES FROM HERE IN 1619 THE
FIRST INDENTURED SERVANTS FROM
AFRICA LANDED ON OUR SHORES AT
ALL POINT, COMFORT WHAT WE CALL
NOW FOR MONROE.
>> ALSO KNOWN AS SLAVERY.
>> YES.
>>Adrianna: A RECENT PLL FROM
THE "WASHINGTON POST" FOUND
THAT 47 PERCENT OF VIRGINIANS
ONE GOVERNOR NORTHAM TO STEP
DOWN.
BUT 47 PERCENT ALSO WANT HIM TO
STAY.
TO KEEP TRACK OF THE STORY AS
IT CHANGES DOWNLOAD THE FREE
ABC7 NEWS APP YOU CAN GET
ALERTS AND SWITCH YOUR PHONE.
MAKE NOW TO A POSSIBILITY OF
ANOTHER GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
THE TEMPORARY FUNDING MEASURES
THAT THE PRESIDENT SIGNED THAT
REOPENED THE GOVERNMENT RUNS
OUT OF FRIDAY AT MIDNIGHT.
NOW THEY ARE WORKING TO AVERT
ANOTHER SHUTDOWN BUT TALKS HAVE
STALLED WITH SERENA MARSHALL
WITH THE JEWS THEY COULD HAMMER
OUT A DEAL.
>>Reporter: DAYS AWAY FROM
ANOTHER SHUTDOWN AND
NEGOTIATIONS ARE STALLED.
>> I THINK THE BIG PROBLEM HERE
IS, THIS HAS BECOME AN EGO
NEGOTIATION AND THIS IS NOT
REALLY OVER SUBSTANCE.
>> THEY HOPE TO ANNOUNCE A DEAL
TODAY BUT THE STICKING POINT IS
NOT JUST OVER THE WALL ANYMORE.
>> THAT WE WERE TRACKING PRETTY
GOOD OVER THE LAST WEEK BUT IT
SEEMS OVER THE LAST 24 HOURS OR
SO THAT THE GOALPOST HAD BEEN
MOVING FROM THE DEMOCRATS.
>> DEMOCRATS NOT WANT ELEMENT
OF THE BEDS OF DETENTION
CENTERS.
REPUBLICANS WANT THE BEST
NUMBER TO GO UP AS PER YOUR
FUNDS DROPPED FROM THE PRESENT
STATEMENT OF $5.7 BILLION WITH
THE PRESENT RESPONDING ON
TWITTER.
WRITING, THE DEMOCRATS DO NOT
WANT US TO DETAIN OR SEND BACK
CRIMINAL ALIENS.
THIS IS A BRAND-NEW DEMAND.
CRAZY.
HIS ACTING CHIEF OF STAFF TOLD
FOX NEWS,
>> THE GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN
INSTANTLY STILL ON THE TABLE.
>> ALSO STILL ON THE TABLE IS A
NATIONAL THAT COULD -- NATIONAL
EMERGENCY DECLARATION.
HIS THE ROAD TO EL PASO, TEXAS.
THE CITY HE TOUTED DURING THE
STATE OF THE UNION AS.
>> IT USED TO HAVE EXTREMELY
HIGH RATES OF VIOLENT CRIME.
>> EL PASO OFFICIALS DENOUNCED
THAT CLAIM AND ACCORDING TO THE
EL PASO TIMES, THE CITY HAD THE
THIRD LOWEST VIOLENT CRIME RATE
AMONG COMPARABLE CITIES BEFORE
CONSTRUCTION BEGAN.> THERE
IS NO APPETITE FOR ANOTHER
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN BUT IT
STILL PUTS THE CHANCE OF IT
HAPPENING ANYWAY AT 50 PERCENT.
SERENA MARSHALL ABC NEWS
WASHINGTON.
>>Adrianna: ACTING DEFENSE
SECTOR IS NOW IN AFGHANISTAN.
THE UNANNOUNCED VISIT IS HIS
FIRST AND HE WILL MEET WITH
U.S. COMMANDERS AND AFGHAN
LEADERS.
SHANAHAN TOLD REPORTERS
TRAVELING WITH HIM THAT HIS
MESSAGE TO AFGHANS IS THAT THEY
MUST ULTIMATELY DECIDE THEIR
OWN FUTURE, INCLUDING HOW PEACE
IS TO BE ACHIEVED WITH THE
TALIBAN.
>>> A CONVICTED SEX OFFENDER IS
CHARGED WITH RAPING A WOMAN HE
MET AT CLYDE'S OF CHEVY CHASE.
POLICE SAY PHILIP KANTOR SAID
IT WOULD BE IN THE WOMAN'S
DRINK AT THE BAR LAST MONTH.
HE IS ACCUSED OF TAKING HER
BACK TO HIS APARTMENT WHERE HE
ATTACKED AND PHOTOGRAPHED HER.
THE WOMAN TOLD POLICE THAT SHE
HAS NO RELATION OF WHAT
HAPPENED FROM THE TIME SHE HAD
TO DRINK UNTIL SHE WOKE UP IN
HIS APARTMENT.
>>> NOW TO THE BLACKMAIL
ALLEGATIONS AGAINST JEFF BEZOS.
THEY APPARENTLY HAVE AN IDEA OF
WHO LEAKED HIS PRIVATE TEXT
MESSAGES AND PHOTOS.
MEANWHILE, IN AN EXCLUSIVE
INTERVIEW THE ATTORNEY FOR
NATIONAL ENQUIRER'S CHIEF
DENIES IT WAS ENGAGING IN
EXTORTION.
MAGGIE RULLI HAS THE LATEST.
>> THE BATTLE BETWEEN THE
WORLD'S RICHEST MAN, JEFF BEZOS
IN THE NATIONAL ENQUIRER
CONTINUES.
>> IT IS ABSOLUTE NOT EXTORTION
OR BLOOD.> THE ATTORNEY FOR
AMIS DETERMINED, THE COMMITTEE
WHO OWNS THE TABLET DENIED
ALLEGATIONS ON THIS WEEK AND
CLAIMS THE PERSON WHO LEAKED
INTIMATE TEXT MESSAGES BETWEEN
BASES AND HIS REPORTED
GIRLFRIEND HAS BEEN A RELIABLE
SOURCE FOR YEARS.
>> IT WAS A SOURCE THAT WAS
WELL-KNOWN TO BOTH MR. BASIS
AND MS. SANCHEZ.
>> ACCORDING TO THE DAILY PIECE
WITH ONE POSSIBLE SOURCE OF THE
LEAK TEXT IS SANCHEZ'S BROTHER,
A VOCAL SUPPORTER OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP.>> IF HE IS, I DO NOT
CONTROL THE POLITICAL ELEMENT
HERE.
>> MICHAEL DENIES THE
ALLEGATIONS.
>> HE CLAIMS THAT THE NATIONAL
ENQUIRER AND THE PARENT COMPANY
FRENCH RELEASE TEXT MESSAGES
AND PICTURES THAT THEY EXCHANGE
UNLESS BASES CALL ALL HIS
INVESTIGATION INTO HOW THEY GOT
THE PHOTOS AND RELEASED A
STATEMENT PUBLICLY DENIED THAT
THEIR PUBLICATION HAD ANY
POLITICAL MOTIVE.
>> THEY SEEM TO BE THE ONES WHO
ARE THE AGGRESSOR.
THEY SEEM TO BE DESPERATE TO
HAVE THIS POLITICAL ELEMENT
BEING RUDE REMOVED FROM THE
STRIP.
>> HOURS AFTER THE PLAYERS
POSE, JOURNALIST TWEETED TAT
WHILE HE WAS LOOK INTO THE
NATIONAL ENQUIRER'S
RELATIONSHIP WITH PRESIDENT
TRUMP, AMI URGED HIM TO STOP
DIGGING OR WE WILL ROUTE YOU.
HE SAYS HE DID NOT.
>> THIS SEEMS LIKE A PATTERN
PRACTICE ACCORDING TO THESE
JOURNALS.
>> I AM NOT AWARE OF ANY
ATTEMPT BY EMPLOYEES OF AMI TO
BLACKMAIL OR COMMIT ANY CRIME
AT ALL.
>> AMI HAS INSISTED ALL ALONG
THAT THEY HAVE OPERATED
LAWFULLY AND IN GOOD FAITH.
BUT THE BOARD IS INVESTIGATING
WITH MAGGIE RULLI ABC NEWS NEW
YORK.
>>Adrianna: COMING UP ON ABC7
NEWS AT NOON.
THEY MAYBE CUTE AND CUDDLY IN
THIS HOLIDAY COKE COMMERCIALS.
LIFE, POLAR BEARS ARE ANYTHING
BUT WARM AND COZY AND THEY ARE
CLOSING IN ON HUMANS.
SEE WHERE THEY HAVE INVADED IN
THE MEASURE BEING TAKEN TO KEEP
A COMMUNITY SAFE.
PLUS THE 61ST ACADEMY AWARDS IN
THE BOOKS.
THIS PRICE GUEST THAT KICKED
OFF THE SHOW.
>>Eric: LOOKING AT THE ROADWAYS
TODAY.SO FAR DESPITE
CONDITIONS OVERALL CONDITIONS
ARE NOT TOO BAD ON THE BIRDS.
IT IS NOT TOO SLICK OUT THERE.
TO WATCH OUT FOR THE CARS ON
FIVE SOUTHBOUND IN VIRGINIA
PAST FAIRFAX COUNTY PARKWAY.
THE TWO RIGHT LANES ARE STILL
BLOCKED OFF AT THIS POINT.
AN OVERTURNED ARMY TRANSPORT
VEHICLE AND THIS IS GOING TO BE
A BIT OF A COMPLICATED SPOT.
SOUTHBOUND TRAFFIC IS VERY
HEAVY APOSTASY AND HEADING DOWN
TO THE BELTWAY AS A RESULT.
TRY TO TAKE A LOOK AT SOME OF
THOSE DELAYS BACK TOWARD THE
SPRING FIELD E
People aren't talking
about how much money
they saved buying
Giant-brand chicken.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
At Giant, it's
the little things
that make mealtime easy,
so you have more time
with the people you love.
People aren't talking
about Giant's
fresh grab and go
salads and sandwiches.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh, hello.
At Giant, it's
the little things
that make mealtime easy,
so you have more time
with the people you love.
>>Adrianna: HAPPENING RIGHT
NOW.
THOUSANDS OF TEACHERS IN DENVER
ARE HITTING THE PICKET LINES
INSTEAD OF HEADING TO CLASS.
THEIR START COMING AFTER TALKS
OF INCREASED SALARY AND BONUSES
WITH PUBLIC SCHOOLS FELL
THROUGH.
CLASSROOMS WILL BE STAFFED BY
DEMONSTRATORS AND SUBSTITUTES.
THE STRIKE SNEERINGLY DISRUPTS
DAY-TO-DAY OPERATIONS AT 207
SCHOOLS WITH 90,000 STUDENTS.
TEACHERS ARE STRUGGLING TO MAKE
ENDS MEET AS THE COST OF LIVING
RISES.
>>> THERE IS AN INVASION
HAPPENING ON A RUSSIA ISLAND BY
POLAR BEARS.
TAKE A LOOK HERE.
STATE OF EMERGENCY HAS BEEN
DECLARED ON A REMOTE ISLAND OFF
OF RUSSIA SCARES BUT THIS AFTER
52 POLAR BEARS WERE SPOTTED
BETWEEN DECEMBER AND FEBRUARY.
A LOT OF THEM LOOKING FOR FOOD
AND FEEDING ON TRASH.
LOCALS HAVE REPORTED SEVERAL
ATTACKS.
THE CONTACT WITH HUMANS HAS
INCREASED AS CLIMATE CHANGE HAS
REDUCED THEIR CIS HABITATS.
SPECIALIST HAS BEEN DEPLOYED TO
SEDATE AND REMOVE MANY OF THOSE
POLAR BEARS.
>>> IS COMING IN ALL TOO OFTEN
OCCURS AT NBA GAMES.
BATS FLYING INTO ARENAS BUT THE
LATEST INCIDENT IS CAUSING A
HEALTH SCARE.
LOOSE BUT FORCING A BRIEF DELAY
DURING THE PACERS CLIPPERS GAME
INDIANA ANIMAL GETTING AWFULLY
CLOSE TO PEOPLE ON THE COURT
AND IN THE STANDS.
HEALTH OFFICIALS TELLING PEOPLE
WHO HAD CONTACT WITH THE BACK
THAT THEY MAY HAVE BEEN EXPOSED
TO BABIES.
JUST LAST MONTH THERE WERE TWO
BACK INCDENTS AT SPURS GAMES
IN SAN ANTONIO.
MAKE IT WAS MUSIC'S PIGMENT AT
THIS IS THE FIRST GRAMMY AWARDS
AND EQUIPMENT AND WRAP ARTIST
OPTION FIGURES BUT LAST NIGHT
BOTH TOOK CENTER STAGE WITH
HISTORIC WINS.
RICK HAS MORE FROM HOLLYWOOD.
>> THIS IS LOVE.
THIS IS LIFE.
THIS IS LIVING.
THIS IS WHITE IN ALL BECAUSE OF
MUSIC.
>> AFTER LAST YEAR'S GRAMMY
AWARDS WERE TAGGED GRAMMY'S SO
MEAL BY THE USE OF SOCIAL
MEDIA.
THE 61ST SCRIMMAGE RESPONDED.
TURNING IT INTO A NED PERME
ABOUT WOMEN.
>> MUSIC SHOWS US THAT ALL OF
IT MATTERS.
EVERY STORY, WITHIN EVERY VOIC
, EVERY NOTE WITHIN EVERY SONG.
>> THE THEME CARRY OVER TO
TRIBUTES TO DOLLY PARTON.
AND DIANA ROSS.
[MUSIC]
>> IT WAS ALSO REFLECTED BY
MANY OF THE BIG WINNERS WITH
SINGER-SONGWRITER BRANDI
CARLISLE ONE THREE AWARDS WHILE
SHE WAS BEST NEW ARTIST.
>> LADY GAGA ONE THREE GRAMS
INCLUDING ONE FOR SHALLOW FROM
A STAR IS BORN.
>> THIS IS AMERICA!
>> TWO ARTIST TIED FOR THE MOST
WORDS WITH FOR EACH.
CHILDERS GAMBINO WAS NOT ON
HAND TO ACCEPT TO ORGANIZE
BIGGEST AWARDS, RECORD AND SONG
OF THE YEAR.
>>
[MUSIC]
>> COUNTRY SINGER CASEY
MUSGRAVE WHO WAS IN ATTENDANCE
ALSO TO COME FOR AWARDS
INCLUDING ALBUM OF THE YEAR.
SUMMING UP THE NIGHT IN THE
INDUSTRY.
>> I WOULD HAVE NOTHING WITHOUT
SONGS, TO ME IT IS ALL ABOUT
THE SONGS.
>> IN HOLLYWOOD I AM RICK.
[MUSIC]
>>Adrianna: I MEAN, YOU WANT TO
SEE TALENT AND THERE IT IS.
GRAMMY'S POST ALICIA KEYS
PLAYING TWO BEAMS AT THE SAME
TIME DURING A TRIBUTE TO MANY
OF HER FAVORITE ARTISTS.
SHE PLAYED SONGS FROM LAUREN
HILL ALL THE WAY TO NOT KING
COLE.
KEYS MILLIE SAID SOCIAL MEDIA
ON FIRE AND IT WAS THE MOST
TALKED ABOUT DURING THE AWARD
SHOW.
SHE IS GOOD AND THAT IS WHAT
SHE DOES.
>>Steve: TALK ABOUT THINGS YOU
CAN LEARN TO DO.
BUT THEN THERE ARE OTHER THINGS
THAT ARE JUST NATURAL TALENT.
>>Adrianna: IN EIGHT.
>>Steve: THAT.
IT IS NATURAL TALENT.
>>Adrianna: SHE CAN PULL IT
OFF.
>>Steve: MY GOODNESS.
>>Adrianna: DID YOU WATCH?
YOU LIKE THE GRAMMYS.
>>Steve: HONESTLY, I DID NOT
KNOW A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE UNTIL
I HEARD THEIR SONGS.
GO FIGURE ON THAT ONE.
IT WAS A GOOD SHOW AND DIANA
ROSS 75 YEARS OLD AND LIVING
LIKE THAT AND LOOKING LIKE
THAT.
TWO THUMBS UP ON THAT ONE.
>>> TODAY IS NOT A TWO THUMBS
UP KIND OF DAY UNLESS YOU LIKE
A CLOUDY, DAMP AND COOL.
HAGERSTON HAD SNOW ON THE
GROUND SO THEY HAD SCHOOL
CANCELLATIONS AND DELAYS.
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE UP
THERE RIGHT NOW THE WINTER
WEATHER ADVISORY THROUGH THIS
AFTERNOON AND THROUGH THE
OVERNIGHT IN TOMORROW MORNING.
NO ACTIVE ADVISORY OVER A
NATURAL HARBOR OVERLOOKING
TOWARD THE WILSON BRIDGE AND
OLD TOWN ALEXANDRIA AT REAGAN
NATIONAL AIRPORT.
CHECK WITH YOUR AIR CARRIER AND
YOU MIGHT FIND A FEW DELAYS AS
ADMITTED TO THE AFTERNOON
BECAUSE OF THE WEATHER.
37 DEGREES AT THE AIRPORT AT
THIS HOUR AND WE STAYED AT 35
IN MANASSAS.
STILL AT THE FREEZING MARK IN
WINCHESTER AND LEESBURG AND 33
IN GAITHERSBURG, AND IS NOW AT
34 DEGREES BUT STORM WATCH 7
SATELLITE AND RADAR IF YOU ARE
LIVING INSIDE THE BELTWAY OR
AROUND THE BELTWAY, BUT WHETHER
DOES CONTINUE.
HEAD OVER TOWARD FREDERICK AND
UP TOWARDS HAGERSTOWN AND A
LITTLE BIT OF LIGHT SNOW AT
THIS TIME.
A LOT OF IT HAVING A HARD TIME
REACHING THE GROUND BUT WE HAVE
RAIN DROPS FALLING FROM THE SKY
RIGHT NOW OVER TOWARD TYSON IN
SILVER SPRING, COLLEGE PARK AND
ALSO DOWN TOWARD OLD TOWN.
AS WE HEAD TO THE AFTERNOON
HOURS WE WILL LOOK FOR AREAS OF
RAIN THAT WILL CONTINUE ALONG
WITH THE WINTRY MIX OFF TOWARD
THE NORTH AND WEST WITH THE
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY DOES
CONTINUE AT THIS TIME TO THE
OVERNIGHT.
PULL OFF TO THE WEST WE ARE
TALKING OFF TO THE NORTH AND
WAS, WINTER STORM WARNINGS FOR
GARRETT AND ALLEGHENY COUNTIES
AND THAT CONTINUES UNTIL 12:00.
WE ALSO HAVE A WINTER STORM
WATCH THE WILL EITHER AGREE TO
AN ADVISOR OR WARNING FOR
MARTINSBURG IN WINCHESTER IN
THE SAME FOR ROMNEY.
HERE IS OUR UPDATED FUTURECAST.
YES, BUT WHETHER DOES CONTINUE
AND WILL BECOME A LITTLE BIT
LATER ON THIS AFTERNOON BUT
WILL PICK UP AGAIN ESPECIALLY
NORTH AND WEST OF TOWN MOVING
TO THE AFTERNOON HOURS INTO THE
EVENING AND OVERNIGHT.
BY EARLY TOMORROW MORNING WE
COULD BE LOOKING AT A BIT OF
WINTRY MIX AND SLEET OFF TOWARD
THE NORTH AND WEST.AS ALL OF
THIS CHANGES OVER TO ALL RAIN
TOMORROW AND WE COULD BE
LOOKING AT A TOTAL OF INCH OF
RAIN BY THE TIME THE SYSTEM
MOVES OUT OF FEAR.
FOR TODAY, KEEP AN UMBRELLA
HANDY IN THE UPPER 30S AND
DINING OUT TONIGHT, WALKING ON
14TH STREET LOOKING AT
TEMPERATURES IN THE MIDDLE TO
UPPER 30S WITH ON AND OFF
SHOWERS TO CONTINUE.
NIGHTTIME LOWS WILL RANGE FROM
32 TO 37 DEGREES.
EARLY TOMORROW MORNING, BE ON
THE LOOKOUT FOR SLICK SPOTS,
ESPECIALLY NORTH AND WEST OF
TOWN.
HOUR BY HOUR FORECAST FOR
TOMORROW DOES SHOW MODERATE
TEMPERATURES.
THEY WILL BE IN THE MIDDLE 40S
FOR DAYTIME HIGHS AND GRABBED
THE UMBRELLA AND YOU WILL NEED
IT.
MODERATE RAIN DURING THE
AFTERNOON THERE WILL CLEAR
THINGS UP.
WHEN YOU KNOW IT?
FOR THE MIDDLE OF THE WEEK 47
ON WEDNESDAY IN VALENTINE'S DAY
IN THE MIDDLE 50S BUT LO
>>Adrianna: WE ARE BACK NOW
WITH THE NEW TWIST BETWEEN THE
FIJI WATER IN THE COMPANY HE
MADE HER FAMOUS.
TJ HOLMES HAS THE DETAILS.
>> SHE IS THE MODEL THAT
LAUNCHED A THOUSAND MEANS.
KELLY STEINBOCK, THE FIJI WATER
GIRL.
SHE PHOTOBOMB HER WAY OUT OF
OBSCURITY AT THIS YEAR'S GOLDEN
GLOBES BY POSING WITH BOTTLES
OF WATER BETWEEN EVERY STAR
THAT SHE COULD FIND WITH HIS IS
BEHIND NICOLE KIDMAN AND HERE
SHE IS AGAIN BETWEEN RICHARD
MADDEN.
HER INSTANT INTERNET FAME ALSO
ENTER AN APPEARANCE IN
LATE-NIGHT.
>> ARE YOU THE GIRL FROM LAST
NIGHT?
>> THAT IS ME.
>> NOW FIJI SAYS HER 15 MINUTES
ARE UP.
THEY FILED A LAWSUIT AGAINST
HER CLAIMING THAT SHE RENEGED
ON A DEAL TO BE A BRAND
AMBASSADOR FOR FIJI.
THERE SHOULD THEY ACCUSE HER OF
TRYING TO CAPITALIZE ON HER
FLEETING 15 MINUTES OF INTERNET
FAME AND EXTORT FIJI BECAUSE
SHE WANTED A BETTER DEAL THAN
THE ORIGINAL $90,000 SHE HAD
ORIGINALLY ACCEPTED.
THE COMPANY'S LAWSUIT IS A
COUNTER TO A LAWSUIT THAT SHE
FILED LAST MONTH.
SHE SUED BG AND ITS PARENT
COMPANY, THEWONDERFUL COMPANY,
FOR NEARLY HALF A MILLION
SAYING THAT THE COMPANIES WERE
TRYING TO CAPITALIZE ON HER
OVERNIGHT FAME , USED HER LIKE
THIS WITHOUT HER PERMISSION TO
CREATE A WORLDWIDE CARDBOARD
CUTOUT MARKETING CAMPAIGN.
>>Adrianna: WHEN WILL WE SEE
SANTA AGAIN?
>>Steve: WEDNESDAY.
HERE WE ARE ON MONDAY THAT IS
48 HOURS AWAY.
HIGH TEMPERATURE TODAY ONLY IN
THE HIGH-40S BUT WE HAVE
TOMORROW ANOTHER RAINY DAY.
IT WILL BE A SLOW GO FOR THE
EARLY MORNING, OR SHOULD SAY
MORE COMMITTED THE MANDATE INTO
THE EVENING AND THEN DISCUSS
WILL BEGIN TO CLEAR IT LITTLE
ON THE WINDY SKY WEDNESDAY AND
VALENTINE'S DAY INTO THE 50S IN
THE NICOLE FRONT ON FRIDAY.
THAT WILL DROP OUT OF RESPECT
DOWN INTO THE 40S.
A WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY FOR
FREDERICK COUNTY AND WASHINGTON
COUNTIES AND IN MARYLAND AND
THAT IS THROUGH TOMORROW
MORNING.
NOT THE BEST OUT THERE BUT IT
IS NOT IMPORTANT AT LEAST AND
THAT IS GOOD.
BE PREPARED IF YOU ARE DRIVING
UP SUNDAY TO
>> YOU ARE WATCHING ABC7 NEWS
AT NOON.
ON YOUR SIDE.
>>Adrianna: YOU KNOW IT IS A
SLOPPY DAY WHEN THE TRACTION ON
YOUR BOOTS IS AS HANDY AS WHAT
IS ON YOUR TIRES.
WE ARE IN FREDERICK WITH A LOOK
AT THE ICE CONDITIONS FOR THOSE
WHO HAD A HEAD OUT EARLY THIS
MORNING.
>> WINTER IS BACK THIS TIME A
MIX OF SLEET AND FREEZING RAIN
HAS US SLIDING INTO THE WEEK.
>> ARE THE SIDEWALK SLIPPERY?
>> NOT ANYMORE.
THEY WERE.
THERE WAS LIKE THAT MUCH ICE.
>> IT IS A DAY WHEN YOUR BOOTS
NEED AS MUCH TRACTION AS YOUR
TIRES PUT.
>> THANK YOU BE A LITTLE BIT
MORE DANGEROUS AND CONSTANT
DRIVING.
WE DO A GOOD JOB TRYING TO
MAINTAIN THE SIDEWALKS BUT
SOMETIMES IT COMES UPON US
QUICKLY DOWN HERE.
>> DOUGLAS HENDERSON HAD TO GET
OUT EARLY TO SHOVEL THE
SIDEWALKS, LINK ICE MELT FIRST
HELPED HIM CLEAR THEM OUT
QUICKLY.
p>> IT IS LIKE BLACK ICE BUT IT
LOOKS WET BUT IT IS SLIPPERY.
>> TAKE A LOOK AT THE SIDEWALKS
NEAR LINCOLN ELEMENTARY IN
DOWNTOWN FREDERICK.
COUNTY SCHOOLS WERE ON A
TWO-HOUR DELAY BEFORE
ADMINISTRATORS TOOK ANOTHER
LOOK AND DECIDED TO CLOSE.
>> WE TOOK STORM TRACK 72 AREAS
NORTH AND WEST OF THE CITY AND
THAT IS WHAT WE NOTICED SLUSHY
ROADS AND ICY SIDEWALKS.
THE MAIN ROADS WERE MRS. --
MOSTLY WHITE.
>> AROUND 5:30 A.M. WE SPOTTED
A BUNCH OF SALT TRUCKS ON
INTERSTATE 70 GOING TO
WASHINGTON IN FREDERICK
COUNTIES. FRESH LAYER OF
SALT HELPED TO MELT THE ICE.
AS WE GET CLOSER TO VALENTINE'S
DAY, SO MANY ARE HOPING THAT
MOTHER NATURE SHOWS US SOME
LOVE.> I WOULD RATHER BE ONE
THING COLD.
>> IN FREDERICK, CHERYL
O'CONNOR ABC7 NEWS.
>>Adrianna: HERE IS A LIVE LOOK
AT I-95 NORTH IN FAIRFAX AND
YOU CAN SEE BAD TRAFFIC THERE.
LOOKS LIKE AN ACCIDENT OFF TO
THE SIDE OF THE ROAD THERE.
THOSE SLICK CONDITIONS CAN STAY
FOR A WHILE.
METEOROLOGIST STEVE RUDIN IS
HERE WITH A CHECK OF THE
FORECAST.
>>Steve: WE ARE LOOKING AT THE
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY FOR
FREDERICK AND WASHINGTON
COUNTIES IN MARYLAND.
OVERLOOKING THE PENTAGON AND
PENTAGON CITY WE HAVE BUT
ROADWAYS AND RAN ACROSS THE
AREA.
A COLBURN, IT DEFINITELY IS BUT
WE ARE LOOKING AT MORE WITH
WEATHER AT GARRETT AND
ALLEGHENY COUNTIES IN WESTERN
MARYLAND.
IF YOUR TRAVELS TAKE YOU THAT
DIRECTION TODAY OVER TOWARD
CUMBERLAND AND FROSTBURG YOU
WANT TO LEAVE MORE TIME.ERE
IS SUNLIGHT SEVEN RADAR.
HEADED TOWARD FREDERICK AND
VERMONT AND PRINCIPAL IN
HAGERSTOWN AND THAT IS WHERE WE
HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF SLEET
MIXED IN WITH THE RAIN AT THIS
HOUR.
ONCE AGAIN, TRAVELING FROM
TYSONS TOWARD SILVER SPRING,
COLLEGE PARK, LOOKING AT WHAT
ROADWAYS BUT IT MIGHT SLOW YOU
DOWN A BIT MOVING TO THE
AFTERNOON HOURS.
TEMPERATURES ARE ABOVE FREEZING
AT REAGAN NATIONAL AIRPORT AND
MOVING THROUGH THIS AFTERNOON
KEEP AN UMBRELLA HEAVY, LEAVE
EXTRA TIME.
UPPER 30S FOR DAYTIME HIGHS.
TALKING ABOUT A MILDER DAY
TOMORROW BUT IT IS GOING TO BE
A BUT ONE AROUND THE DMV.
WE DO HAVE CLEARING SKIES ON
THE WAY AND I WILL SHOW YOU THE
FRESHLY UPDATED SUNDAY OUTLOOK
COMING UP IN A FEW MINUTES.
>>Adrianna: NOW TO THE LATEST
OUT OF IRGINIA.
GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM SPEAKING
OUT ABOUT THE POLITICAL CHAOS
THAT HAS GRIPPED HIS STATE AND
THE FUTURE.
WE CONTINUE OUR TEAM COVERAGE
FROM RICHMOND.
>> VIRGINIA'S GOVERNOR RALPH
NORTHAM BREAKING HIS SILENCE IN
REFUSING CALLS TO RESIGN, BUT
ADMITTING THAT HE THOUGHT ABOUT
LEAVING OFFICE.
>> YES, I HAVE THOUGHT ABOUT
RESIGNING, BUT I HAVE ALSO
THOUGHT ABOUT WHAT VIRGINIA
NEEDS RIGHT NOW.
I REALLY FEEL LIKE I AM IN A
POSITION WHERE I CAN TAKE
CONTINUE TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
>> CRITICS SAY, EVEN IN HIS
FIRST TV INTERVIEW SINCE THE
SCANDAL BROUGHT WITH HIM AND HE
STILL SOUNDS OUT OF TOUCH.
>> JUST 90 MILES FROM HERE AND
IN 1619, THE FIRST INDENTURED
SERVANTS FROM AFRICA LANDED ON
OUR SHORES AT OPEN COMFORT, BUT
WE CALL NOW FORT MONROE.
>> ALSO KNOWN AS SLAVERY.
>> YES.
WHILE WE HAVE MADE A LOT OF
PROGRESS IN VIRGINIA, SLAVERY
HAS ENDED, SCHOOLS HAVE BEEN
DESEGREGATED WE HAVE AND THE
JIM CROW LAWS.
EASIER ACCESS TO VOTING.
IT IS ABUNDANTLY CLEAR THAT WE
STILL HAVE A LOT OF WORK TO DO.
>> HIS PROBLEMS START.
THIS RAISES FEDERAL FROM HIS
MEDICAL SCHOOL FACEBOOK PAGE.
HE DID ADMIT TO APPEARING ONCE
IN BLACK ICE BUT SAYS HE IS NOT
ONE OF THOSE TWO MEN.
>> COMPLICATING THE MATTER IS,
VIRGINIA'S LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR
JUSTIN FAIRFAX HAS NOW BEEN
ACCUSED OF TWO WOMEN OF SEXUAL
ASSAULT, WHICH HE NOW DENIES
POLITICAL SCIENCE PROFESSOR
VANESSA TYSON SAID HE FORCED
HER TO PERFORM A SEX ACT IN
2004.
MEREDITH WATSON SAYS FAIRFAX
SEXUALLY ASSAULTED HER WHILE
BOTH WERE STUDENTS AT DUKE
UNIVERSITY IN 2000.> IF
THESE TRANSITIONS ARE
DETERMINED TO BE TRUE I DO NOT
THINK HE WILL HAVE ANY OTHER
OPTION BUT TO RESIGN.
>> OTHERS ARE DONE GIVING
FAIRFAX ANYMORE CHANCES,
INCLUDING FELLOW DEMOCRATS.
>> HE NEEDS TO RESIGN
IMMEDIATELY.SHOULD THE
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR FAILED TO
DO SO, ON MONDAY I INTEND TO
INTRODUCE ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENT ON LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR JUSTIN FAIRFAX.
>>Adrianna: ATTORNEYS FOR BOTH
WOMEN, MEREDITH WATSON AND
VANESSA TYSON SAID THEY ARE
WILLING TO TESTIFY IF AN
IMPEACHMENT HEARING MOVES
FORWARD FAIRFAX HAS VEHEMENTLY
DENIED BOTH ALLEGATIONS AND
ASKING FOR DUE PROCESS AND ALSO
ASKING THAT NO ONE RUSH TO
JUDGMENT.
MAKE A NEW PULL FROM THE
"WASHINGTON POST" SHOWS JUST
HOW DIVIDED BETWEEN IS ON THIS
POLITICAL SCANDAL.
47 PERCENT OF RESIDENTS WANTED
GOVERNOR NORTHAM TO STAND DOWN
AND 47 PERCENT BUT HIM TO STAY
IN OFFICE.
EXPERTS SAY THAT MIGHT MAKE IT
A CHALLENGE FOR THE GOVERNOR TO
GET THINGS DONE FOR THE REST OF
HIS TERM.
>> THE GOVERNOR WAS THINKING
VERY SERIOUSLY ABOUT WHETHER HE
COULD BE EFFECTIVE IN THE ROLE
AS GOVERNOR.
AND YET, THE SURVEY DATA SHOWED
THAT THE CORE OF THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY AND ALSO
AFRICAN-AMERICANS IN THE STATE
ARE SUPPORTING HIM TO STAY IN
OFFICE.
>>Adrianna: DESPITE THOSE
POCKETS OF SUPPORT, 7/10
VIRGINIANS SAY THE GOVERNOR
STATEMENT ABOUT THE RACIST
YEARBOOK PHOTO ARE NOT
BELIEVABLE AND OTHERS SAY HE
WILL BE EFFECTIVE FOR THE THREE
YEARS LEFT IN HIS TERM.
>>> NOW TO AN ABC NEWS
EXCLUSIVE.
NEVER BEFORE HEARD AUDIOTAPES
OF ADMISSION THE COMMITTEE
ADMITTED RUSSIA.
>> IT IS VERY HARD.T IS SO
MUCH PAIN.
>> YOU ARE LISTENING TO THE
VOICE OF MARIA BUTINA, THE GUN
CLUB AND GRADUATE STUDENT AND
RUSSIAN NATIONAL ACCUSED OF
COURTING CONSERVATIVE ELITE AND
POWER PLAYERS IN THE NRA ON
BEHALF OF THE KREMLIN.
THIS MORNING WE ARE HEARING THE
30-YEAR-OLD SPEAK FOR THE FIRST
TIME SINCE HER JULY ARREST.
DEFENDING HERSELF AGAINST
ALLEGATIONS THAT SHE WAS
WORKING AS A COVERT FORD AGENT.
>> YOU WOULD NEVER SEE ME IN
PUBLIC.
I WOULD BE THE MOST UNSEEN
PERSON ON EARTH.
>> SHE RECORDED THIS DUET WITH
AN NRA INSIDER AFTER THEY
BECAME ROMANTICALLY INVOLVED.
SHE SPENT TIME WITH AUTHOR AND
JOURNALIST JIM BELFORD DURING
THE LAST MONTHS OF HER FREEDOM.
BAMFORD RECORDING THEIR
CONVERSATIONS FOR A PIECE IN
THE LATEST ISSUE OF THE NEW
REPUBLIC TITLE, THE SPY WHO
WASN'T.
>> WE HAVE HAD A NUMBER OF LONG
INTERVIEWS, BUT ONE TIME SHE
JUST NEVER SHOWED UP.
THE NEXT DAY SHE APOLOGIZED AND
SHE SAID THE FBI HAD RATED HER
APARTMENT.
>> WAS THERE POUNDING ON THE
DOOR?
DID THEY HEAL FBI?
>> YES THEY SAID THEY HAD A
SEARCH WARRANT.
THEY PUSHED ME IN.
>> A PAMPERED CHEF IS NEVER
BEFORE SEEN PHOTOS TAKEN IN THE
AFTERMATH OF THE RAID.
>> SHE WAS REALLY FRIGHTENED BY
IT ALL.
>> AFTER SHE WAS ARRESTED, HER
CONVERSATIONS WITH HIM
CONTINUED FROM BEHIND BARS.
>> I EXERCISE AND I READ IN A
SLEEP.
I AM ONLINE FOR 22 HOURS A GOOD
TWO HOURS AT NIGHT TO DO
EVERYTHING.
>> IN DECEMBER SHE CUT A DEAL
WITH FEDERAL PROSECUTORS,
PLEADING GUILTY TO CONSPIRACY
TO ACT AS A FOREIGN AGENT.UT
HE BELIEVES THAT SHE IS JUST
LOOKING FOR A WAY OUT.
>> THINK SHE IS PROBABLY HOPING
THAT THIS MAY BRING AN END TO
IT AND SHE WILL GO BACK TO
RUSSIA IN THIS WILL BE A
NIGHTMARE THAT IS OVER.
>>Adrianna: PROSECUTORS SAY SHE
IS COOPERATING WITH THEM BUT
SAYS SHE IS A FLIGHT RISK.
MEANWHILE, SHE CLAIMS SHE WAS
NEVER INTERVIEWED BY SPECIAL
COUNSEL ROBERT MUELLER'S
OFFICE.
AS PART OF THE INVESTIGATION
INTO RUSSIAN ELECTION MEDDLING.
>>> MANY OF US KNOW THAT BIG
BROTHER IS ALWAYS WATCHING BUT
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN WHAT HE SEES
GETS SHARED WITH PEOPLE WHO
MAKE IMPORTANT DECISIONS ABOUT
OUR FUTURE?
IT IS ALREADY HAPPENING IN
CHINA AND AS OUR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT KRISTINE FRAZAO
REPORTS, SOMETHING THE U.S.
COULD BE NEXT.
>> FROM WHAT WE EAT TO WHERE WE
GO TO WHO OUR FRIENDS ARE.
THE DATA COLLECTED ON EACH OF
US IS EXPANSIVE SAYS FORMER
SECRETARY OF HOMELAND SECURITY.
>> THEY KNOW WHO YOUR FRIENDS
ARE, WHAT YOUR FRIENDS DO, BUT
YOU ARE DOING ONLINE.
NOW WE HAVE FACIAL RECOGNITION
THEY CAN TELL WHERE YOU ARE
GOING.
>> IN CHINA, INFORMATION LIKE
THIS IS USED TO GIVE EACH
PERSON, WHAT IS CALLED A SOCIAL
CREDIT SCORE.
FOR EVERY MOVE YOU MAKE IS
MONITORED AND SCORED.
IF YOUR SCORE GETS TOO LOW, YOU
MAYBE PREVENTED FROM GETTING A
JOB, TRAVELING BY AIR OR
HIGH-SPEED RAIL.T MAY EVEN
HURT YOUR CHILDREN'S CHANCES OF
GETTING INTO COLLEGE.
>> THE PROGRAM IS CURRENTLY
BEING TESTED IN CHINA WITH AN
OFFICIAL WILL UPDATE OF 2020.
FOR THE PURPOSE OF QUOTE,
CARING FOR SINCERITY AND
TRADITIONAL VIRTUES.
USING ENCOURAGEMENT TO KEEP
TRUST AND CONSTRAINTS AGAINST
BREAKING TRUST AS INCENTIVE
MECHANISMS.
HE NOW RUNS THE CONSULTING
COMPANY SAYS THERE ARE ALREADY
CLAIMS OF SOCIAL SCORING HERE
IN THE UNITED STATES.
>> WE ARE BEGINNING TO SEE IT
ALREADY.
INSURANCE COMPANIES AFFECT YOUR
PREMIUM BASED ON WHETHER YOU
ARE EATING HEALTHY, GETTING A
GOOD NIGHT SLEEP AND EXERCISE.
>> SAYS THE NEED FOR CONGRESS
TO ACT IS URGENT BUT THE
EMPHASIS NEEDS TO CHANGE FROM
HOW DO WE KEEP THINGS
CONFIDENTIAL, BECAUSE FRIENDLY
FOR MANY OF US, IT IS TOO LATE
FOR THAT.
INSTEAD PASS LAWS ON WHO
CONTROLS THE DATA ONCE IT HAS
BEEN GENERATED.
IN WASHINGTON I AM KRISTINE
FRAZAO.
>>Adrianna: COMING UP ON ABC7
NEWS AT NOON.
WE SHOWED YOU THE STATE
>>Adrianna: BACK NOW WITH THE
GLITZ AND GLAMOUR OF THE GRAMMY
AWARDS.
CAUGHT UP WITH THE BIGGEST
NOMINEES ON THE RED CARPET.
>> MUSIC BIGGEST NIGHT
SPONSORED SOME OF THE BREAD
CARPETS MRS. LING AND THE
SURPRISING FASHION.ITH
CARDIAC BE IN THE CENTERPIECE.
IT TOOK THE RED CARPET BY
STORM.
DRAWING COMPARISONS TO
BOTTICELLI'S VENUS AND THE
LITTLE MERMAID IS URSULA.
KENNY PERRY IN PINK MAKING FUN
OF THE MEANS BY POSTING THEM ON
HER INSTAGRAM.
AND JAYLA ROCKING THIS HAD
POSTED WITH LADY GAGA.
IT WAS A RED CARPET TO
REMEMBER.
OUR CAMERAS WERE THERE.E HAD
A ONE ON ONE WITH CASEY
MUSGRAVE JUST AFTER SHE WON THE
BEST COUNTRY SONG.
>> THAT IS SO BALD TO ME
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE WHEN ALL OF
THIS GOES AWAY, IT IS ALL ABOUT
THE SONGS BUT IT ALL STARTED
BECAUSE OF THE SONGS BUT I
WOULD NOT HAVE ANYTHING WITHOUT
SONG.
>> IN ALL SHE TO COME FOUR
GRAMS INCLUDING ALBUM OF THE
YEAR.
>> THIS IS IT!
OH MY GOSH!
I AM EXCITED.
>> THE GRAMMY GOES TO, GOLDEN
HOUR CASEY MUSGRAVE!
>> THE MOST TREATED MOMENT OF
THE NIGHT IS WHEN A POP
SUPERGROUP BTS TOOK THE STAGE
FOR THE FIRST TIME TO PRESENT
BEST OR IN THE ALBUM, TELLING
ME THIS ON THE RED CARPET.
>> TO ALL OUR FANS, THANK YOU
FOR MAKING THIS DREAM COME
TRUE.
>> K POP GROUP AND MOST POPULAR
BOY BAND IN THE WORLD, CALLED
MULTIPLE TIMES SING-ALONG WITH
MILEY CYRUS AND DOLLY PARTON.
>> BROTHERS OSBORNE TELLING ME
ON THE RED CARPET HOW EVERYONE
HERE TELLS -- FEELS ABOUT
DOLLY.
>> YOU HAVE GOT TO SEE DOLLY.
I ALWAYS THINK THE BEST ARTISTS
ARE REALLY JOURNALISTS AND SHE
IS.
SHE FITS IN THE CATEGORY OF
COUNTRY MUSIC, BUT WHO DOES NOT
THINK DOLLY PARTON SCHOOL?
EVERYBODY LOVES DOLLY.
>> I WANT TO BE DOLLY.
>> THE ALWAYS COOL BACKSTREET
BOYS NOMINATED FOR THE EIGHTH
TIME.
THEY DID NOT TAKE HOME ANY
AWARDS BUT WITH A NUMBER ONE
ALBUM IN THE BOOK RIGHT NOW, I
WOULD SAY THEY ARE STILL
WINNING.
>> WHAT YOU THINK IS THE SECRET
COMING TO COME BACK WHEN YOU
NEVER REALLY LEFT BUT IT IS
LIKE YOU RESEARCHED AND CAME
THIS FORCE THAT IS UNSTOPPABLE.
>> PERSEVERANCE IN WORKING
HARD.
NOT GIVING UP.
>> CHEMISTRY, PASSION.OVE.
WE LOVE WHAT WE DO.
>> THE LOVE FOR ONE ANOTHER AS
WELL.
AND OUR FANS.
>>Adrianna: DOES THAT MAKE YOU
FEEL OLD?
BACKSTREET BOYS?
>>Steve: THEY ARE LIKE MY AGE.
>>> THE WEATHER TODAY'S LITTLE
BIT ON THE GLOOMY SIDE AND
TOMORROW ANOTHER WHAT DAY ON
THE WAY.
WE HAVE BETTER WEATHER ON THE
WAY LATER ON THIS WEEK.ET
THE WORST OF IT OVER WITH NOW
AND THEN WE ENJOY THE REST OF
THE WEEK.
OVERLY NATIONAL CATHEDRAL FROM
OUR CAMERA WE HAVE READ ACROSS
THE AREA AND THE BEACHES
LOOKING AT RAINDROPS AT THIS
ARE NOT THE REAL ESTATE BUT
BEING BY THE OCEAN SOUNDS NICE.
REAGAN NATIONAL AIRPORT WITH A
LITTLE BIT OF FALLING OUT
THERE.
IF YOU ARE TRAVELING TODAY MAKE
SURE YOU LEAVE AN EXTRA FEW
MINUTES TO GET FROM POINT A TO
POINT B AS YOU MAY SLOW THINGS
DOWN BECAUSE OF THE WET
PAVEMENT.
ABOVE FREEZING IN DOWNTOWN D.C.
AND 32 DEGREES RIGHT AT THE
PRISON WORK IN LEESBURG IN THE
SAME OVER AT WINCHESTER, LORI
AND MAKING IT UP TO 34.
LOOKING AT 37 OVER AT ANNAPOLIS
AND READ THE FREEZING MARK AT
BWI MARSHALL.
STORM WATCH 7 SATELLITE AND
RADAR FILLING IN WITH PLENTY OF
RAIN INSIDE AND ON THE OUTSIDE
OF THE BELTWAY.
RAIN MAKES HIM A LITTLE BIT OF
SLEET AND SNOW.
WHEN TREATMENTS FOR FREDERICK
AND FAIRMONT AND OVER TOWARD
HAGERSTOWN.
THE WET ROADWAYS WILL STICK
AROUND, NOT ONLY FOR THIS
AFTERNOON BUT IN THE EVENING
RUSH HOUR COMMUTE.
AND THEN INTO THE OVERNIGHT.
ONCE AGAIN, LEAVE EXTRA TIME.
IF YOU HAVE THE LUXURY.
ALSO BE SURE TO NOTE THAT WE
HAVE WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY
NOT ONLY THROUGH THIS AFTERNOON
BUT INTO TONIGHT AND THEN INTO
EARLY TOMORROW MORNING.
FREDERICK COUNTY ALSO INTO
WASHINGTON COUNTY AND INCLUDES
HAGERSTOWN.
THEN THE WINTER STORM WARNING
FOR GARRETT AND ALLEGHENY
COUNTY IS OVER TOWARD
CUMBERLAND AND FROSTBURG.
THAT IS UNTIL NOON TOMORROW.
MR. MARCH FOR RALEIGH AND
WINCHESTER WILL LIKELY UPGRADE
TO PUT WEATHER ADVISORY AS WE
MOVE INTO THE OVERNIGHT HOURS
AND THEN EARLY TOMORROW
MORNING.
HERE IS THE FUTURECAST THAT HAS
JUST UPDATED FOR US.
HE DOES WANT TO KEEP BUT
WHETHER IN OUR FORECAST, THE
NORTHERN HALF OF THE CAPITAL
BELTWAY 4:00 THEN WE WILL HEAR
WINTRY MIX ALONG THE
MASON-DIXON LINE.
BY 8:00 P.M. TONIGHT.
THIS WILL ALSO BACK IN WITH
RAIN AND MODERATE TIMES, EARLY
TOMORROW MORNING AND THROUGH
THE AFTERNOON HOURS WITH 12
NOON, 24 HOURS FROM NOW AND WE
ARE STILL DEALING WITH WHAT
WEATHER AROUND THE DMV.
FINALLY WE GET THIS OUT OF HERE
LATELY TOMORROW NIGHT AND THEN
SKIES WILL BEGIN TO CLEAR BUT
IT WILL TURN WINDY FOR
WEDNESDAY.
SO, LUNCH TIME TODAY.
IF YOU ARE GOING TO BE OUT AND
ABOUT.
GRAB AN UMBRELLA AND LEAVE
EXTRA TIME AND WILL BE IN THE
UPPER 30S.
DINNERTIME HOUR IT WILL BE
TEMPERATURES IN THE UPPER 30S
WITH AREAS OF RAIN ONCE AGAIN.
NICE FLOW RATE FROM 32 TO 37
DEGREES WITH TEMPERATURES
AROUND THE FREEZING MARK AND
EVEN BELOW ON THE I-81 CORRIDOR
AND ALONG I-70. BE EXTRA
CAREFUL WITH WHAT SERVICES THAT
HAVE NOT BEEN TREATED AND THE
SLICK ROADWAYS ARE A
POSSIBILITY, EARLY TOMORROW
MORNING.
LISTEN TO WARM THINGS UP FROM
THE LOWER TO MIDDLE 40S WITH
HIGHS TOMORROW AND WILL BE ABLE
TO STAY WITH UPWARDS OF AN INCH
OF RAIN FOR THE TIME THE SYSTEM
FINALLY MOVES OUT OF HERE.
HERE'S A LOOK AT OUR FORECAST.
THE NEXT SEVEN DAYS.
43 TOMORROW AND 47 ON WEDNESDAY
AND VALENTINE'S DAY IN THE
MIDDLE 50S BUT AT LEAST IT WILL
BE DRY.
OUR NEXT BEST CHANCE FOR WHAT
>>Adrianna: EVEN IF YOU WANT TO
WORK OUT.
GETTING TO THE GYM CAN BE A
CHALLENGE BUT THAT IS WHY SOME
CLASSES WILL COME TO YOU.
WE CHECK OUT THIS TREND SEE DO
NOT WASTE YOUR MONEY.
>> THESE DAYS FOLKS IN THE D.C.
AREA STREAM EVERYTHING ON TVS
AND SMART PHONES BUT THE NEWEST
TREND IS STREAMING LIVE GYM
CLASSES AT HOME.
ONE COMPANY IS CASHING IN WITH
NEWCOMERS EVERY DAY.
THE IT IS BUT AS JANE FONDA IN
THE 90S RICHARD SIMMONS.
WITH THE MILLENNIUM CAME
KICKBOXING.
NOW IN 2019 THE HOTTEST WORKOUT
TREND IS A JAM STREAM TO YOUR
HOME.
DAVID IS IN A LIVE CLASS, NOT
AT THE GYM BUT AT HOME.
>> I DO NOT HAVE TO PACK A GYM
BAG OR A CHANGE OF CLOTHES BUT.
>> HE IS ONE OF THOUSANDS TO
JOIN THE PILOT ON WORKOUT
PROGRAM.
PROTON STREAMS LIVE IN
ON-DEMAND SPIN BIKING CLASSES
ACROSS THE WORLD.
>> EXERCISE BIKES HAVE BEEN
AROUND FOR DECADES BUT THIS IS
REALLY THE FIRST TIME THAT A
LIVE GYM CLASS COMES RIGHT TO
YOUR HOME.
>> IT IS NEEDED BECAUSE THE
INSTRUCTORS CAN SEE YOUR
USERNAME SO THEY CAN ALWAYS
GIVE YOU A SHOUT OUT IF IT IS
YOUR BIRTHDAY OR IF IT IS A
SPECIAL RIDE.
>> HE ADMITS IT IS NOT CHEAP.
A BIKE IS $2000 IN CLASSES COST
$39 A MONTH, SIMILAR TO A REAL
GEM.
DESPITE THE COST IT IS SO
POPULAR AND IT HAS CREATED A
COMMUNITY WHERE DAVID HAS MADE
A NEW GROUP OF FRIENDS.
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE
WHO ARE OUT THERE STRUGGLING
WITH SOMETHING.
WHETHER IT IS WEIGHT LOSS OR
WHETHER IT IS WHAT SOMEBODY
MIGHT BE BATTLING CANCER.HIS
COMMUNITY REALLY ROWS BEHIND
IT.
>> OTHER WORKOUT BUSINESSES ARE
MOVING TO THE STREAMING MODEL
TO BUT WITH SMALL STORES AND
TOP-OF-THE-LINE EQUIPMENT IS
THE LEADER WRITER AND MAKES
WORKOUT DVDS LOOK LIKE A OLD
VHS TAPE OF $2000 IS TOO STEEP
FOR YOU.
THIS INTO CHECK OF OTHER
VIRTUAL GEMS LIKE BEACH PARTY,
STREAM CLASSES WITHOUT THE
BICYCLE.
SO YOU DO NOT WASTE YOUR MONEY
♪ We buy any car ♪
♪ Any make, any model,
any age, any price ♪
♪ From 50 bucks to 100 grand ♪
♪ We buy any car ♪
♪ Any, any, any, any ♪
At webuyanycar.com,
the gimmicks stop with our ads.
Trading in our selling
your car is hassle-free
with just three easy steps.
One, get your free
online valuation.
Two, drive to your local
car buying centre.
And three,
walk out with your check
in as little as 30 minutes.
So don't wait.
Get your free online
valuation now.
♪ Find out how much
your car's worth ♪
♪ At webuyanycar.com ♪
>>Adrianna: WE WERE JUST THINK
WE ARE READY FOR SUMMER.
>>Steve: A LITTLE BIT OF GREEN
AND SOME SUNSHINE.
SUNSHINE AS WE MOVE THROUGH
WEDNESDAY BUT WERE ONLY OUT
MONDAY.
IT WINTRY MIX WILL CONTINUE TO
THE NORTH AND WEST OF TOWN.
WE HAVE WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY
FOR FREDERICK IN THE
SURROUNDING COUNTIES.
RAIN MODERATE TIMES DURING THE
AFTERNOON HOURS AND IT WILL BE
WINDY BUT MODERATE ON WEDNESDAY
THE UPPER 40S.
JON HUSTED IS LOOKING GOOD IF
YOU ARE GOING TO BE OUT AND
ABOUT AND THE TEMPERATURES WILL
BE IN THE MID-50S AND MID-50S
ON FRIDAY WITH THE BETTER
CHANCE FOR WHAT WEATHER LATER
IN THE DAY.
AS A CALL FROM MR. AND THAT IS
GOING TO DROP OUR TEMPERATURES
FOR THE UPCOMING WEEKEND.
BILL KELLY WILL BE IN AT 4:00
AND HE WILL HAVE A FRESH UPDATE
ON OUR FUTURECAST AND WHAT TO
EXPECT FOR TONIGHT.
WE ARE WAITING FOR THE WINTER
STORM WATCH OFF TO THE NORTH
AND WEST OF US TO CONVERT TO
EITHER WINTER WEATHER ADVISORY
OR WINTER STORM WARNING.
OR MAYBE IT WILL JUST
DISAPPEAR.
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>> TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS AS WE
COME ON THE AIR.
THE FLIGHT TO THE U.S. BOUND FOR
PHILADELPHIA GROUNDED BEFORE IT
COULD TAKE OFF.
ABC NEWS LEARNING JUST MOMENTS
AGO ONE OF THE AMERICAN AIRLINES
PILOTS WAS ARRESTED.
WHAT WE'RE LEARNING RIGHT NOW.
>>> ALSO BREAKING, FIVE REPORTED
TORNADOES AT THIS HOUR.
THE DEADLY STORM MOVING ACROSS
THE COUNTRY.
20 STATES FROM THE DAKOTAS ALL
THE WAY TO THE NORTHEAST
EXPECTING SNOW, ICE AND
FLOODING.
WHITEOUT CONDITIONS, CARS SWEPT
AWAY.
TONIGHT, THE RESCUES, YOU'LL SEE
THEM.
AND ROB HAS THE NEW TRACK.
>>> THE POLITICAL CRISIS IN
VIRGINIA.
UNBELIEVABLY GROWING YET AGAIN
TONIGHT.
FIRST, THE GOVERNOR, THEN THE
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR, THEN THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL.
AND TONIGHT, ANOTHER TOP STATE
LAWMAKER NOW FACING SERIOUS
QUESTIONS.
>>> THE MURDER MYSTERY OUTSIDE
NEW YORK CITY.
THE WOMAN'S BODICE COVERED IN A
SUITCASE.
TONIGHT, WHAT WE'VE NOW LEARNED.
>>> THE URGENT MANHUNT THIS
EVENING FOR THE GUNMAN AFTER A
WIFE WAS KILLED WHILE SETTING UP
FOR A GARAGE SALE.
>>> THE HORRIFIC CASE OF
APPARENT ROAD RAGE.
THE DRIVER OPENING FIRE ON A
SCHOOL BUS, HITTING THE DRIVER
TWICE.
A YOUNG STUDENT ONBOARD.
>>> THE ABC NEWS EXCLUSIVE
TONIGHT IN THE JAYME CLOSS CASE.
SHE WAS ABDUCTED FOR 88 DAYS.
TONIGHT, YOU WILL HEAR FROM THE
ALLEGED KIDNAPPER'S FATHER.
AND HIS VISITS TO THAT HOUSE
WHILE JAYME CLOSS WAS BEING HELD
CAPTIVE UNDER A BED WHAT HIS
ALLEGEDLY DID TO KEEP HER FROM
YELLING FOR HELP.
>>> AND A DEVELOPING STORY ON
JEFF BESOES, ACCUSING "THE
NATIONAL INYEARER".
WHAT HE'S NOW SAYING.
>>> AND TONIGHT, RIGHT HERE, WE
CELEBRATE A BASEBALL LEGEND, A
TRAIL BLAZER AND HIS REMARKABLE
CAREER.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH
US HERE TONIGHT.
WE HAVE SEVERAL DEVELOPING
STORIES, AND WE BEGIN TONIGHT
WITH AMAZON CEO JEFF BEZOS, IN A
BATTLE WITH NATIONAL ENQUIRER.
TONIGHT, HE HAS JUST GONE PUBLIC
WHAT WITH HE SAYS WAS AN
EXTORTION PLOT INVOLVING
COMPROMISING PHOTOS.
WLET'S GET RIGHT TO REBECCA
JARVIS, WHO HAS BEEN FOLLOWING
THIS STORY, EVERY DEVELOPMENT,
WITH WHAT WE'RE LEARNING
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: THIS IS A STUNNING
TURN IN THAT ONGOING BATTLE
BETWEEN JEFF BEZOS AND THE
NATIONAL ENQUIRER.
JUST WEEKS AGO, THIS WAS THE
STORY, THAT THE NATIONAL
ENQUIRER FIRST BROKE ABOUT HIS
AFFAIR.
HE'S NOW QUESTIONED, WAS THAT
POLITICALLY MOTIVATED?
HE'S COME FORWARD TONIGHT
SUGGESTING THAT THE NATIONAL
ENQUIRER WAS TRYING TO BLACKMAIL
AND EXTORT HIM WITH NUDE PHOTOS.
IN A POST TONIGHT, HE SAYS, OF
COURSE, I DON'T WANT THOSE
PHOTOS PUBLISHED, BUT I DON'T
WANT TO PARTICIPATE IN HIS
WELL-KNOWN PRACTICE OF
BLACKMAIL.
WE REACHED OUT TO THE NATIONAL
ENQUIRER, THEY'VE YET TO
RESPOND, DAVID.
>> ALL RIGHT, REBECCA JARVIS
LEADING US OFF TONIGHT.
REBECCA, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS ANOTHER DEVELOPING
HEADLINE AS WE COME ON TONIGHT.
THE ARREST OF AN AMERICAN
AIRLINES PILOT.
THE FLIGHT WAS BOUND FOR THE
U.S., FOR PHILADELPHIA, IN FACT.
THE PASSENGER JET DID NOT TAKE
OFF FROM THE UK.
ONE OF THE PILOTS WAS TAKEN INTO
CUSTODY ON SUSPICION OF BEING
OVER THE LIMIT FOR ALCOHOL
BEFORE FLYING.
ABC'S SENIOR TRANSPORTATION
CORRESPONDENT DAVID KERLEY WITH
THAT STORY.
>> Reporter: BRITISH AUTHORITIES
DETAINED THE AMERICAN AIRLINES
FLIGHT CREW MEMBER IN MANCHESTER
BEFORE THE A-330 TOOK OFF FOR
PHILADELPHIA.
AN AVIATION SOURCE TELLING ABC
NEWS, IT WAS ONE OF THE THREE
PILOTS, BUT IT IS UNCLEAR IF IT
WAS THE CAPTAIN OR ONE OF THE
FIRST OFFICERS WHO TONIGHT IS
BEING INVESTIGATED FOR
"SUSPICION OF PERFORMING AN
AVIATION FUNCTION WHEN OVER THE
PRESCRIBED LIMIT OF ALCOHOL."
AMERICAN CANCELED THAT FLIGHT,
REBOOKING PASSENGERS AND SAYING
IN A STATEMENT, "SAFETY IS OUR
HIGHEST PRIORITY AND WE
APOLOGIZE TO OUR CUSTOMERS."
THE LIMIT FOR ALCOHOL IN PILOTS
IS HALF THAT FOR DRIVERS, .04.
THIS PILOT ARRESTED TWO YEARS
AGO IN DETROIT.
AND SOME LIKE THIS FORMER
JETBLUE PILOT FACED FEDERAL
CHARGES.
DID YOU PUT 270 PASSENGERS AT
RISK?
>> NO COMMENT.
>> THIS IS AN ONGOING ISSUE
YOU'VE REPORTED ON BEFORE.
DAVID KERLEY WITH US TONIGHT.
WE'RE AWARE OF THIS LATEST
ARREST, AND HAS AMERICAN
AIRLINES TAKEN ANY ACTION, OTHER
THAN CANCELING THE FLIGHT,
DAVID?
>> Reporter: NO, SO FAR, THAT'S
ALL THEY'VE DONE.
AMERICAN SAYS THEY ARE
COOPERATING WITH THE BRITISH
AUTHORITIES WHO ARE
INVESTIGATING THIS INCIDENT.
DAVID?KERLEY, THANK YOU.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT, THE DEADLY
STORM ON THE MOVE AT THIS HOUR.
50 MILLION AMERICANS UNDER
WINTER WEATHER ADVISORIES.
BLIZZARD CONDITIONS, SNOW, ICE
AND AT LEAST FIVE REPORTED
TORNADOES AT THIS HOUR.
BLIZZARD WARNINGS AND BLINDING
SNOW IN MINNESOTA.
LIGHTNING, PART OF AN ICE STORM
IN MISSOURI, COATING TREES,
DOWNING BRANCHES AND POWER LINES
THERE.
CARS IN THIS BUS UNDER WATER IN
TENNESSEE.
AND FIERCE WINDS DERAILING TRAIN
CARS IN MISSOURI.
20 STATES FROM THE DAKOTAS DOWN
TO TENNESSEE, ALL THE WAY UP TO
THE NORTHEAST.
WHERE IT HITS TONIGHT.
ABC'S ALEX PEREZ IN THE STORM
ZONE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, DARING
HIGH WATER RESCUES ACROSS MIDDLE
TENNESSEE.
THAT POWERFUL WINTER STORM
DUMPING A MONTH'S WORTH OF RAIN
IN JUST HOURS.
FIRST RESPONDERS USING
FLASHLIGHTS TO REACH THIS
SUBMERGED CAR, PICKING TWO
PEOPLE TO SAFETY.
>> WE'RE GOING TO NEED SOME
HANDS GETTING THEM UP THE HILL.
>> Reporter: AT LEAST ONE PERSON
SWEPT AWAY AND KILLED ELSEWHERE
IN THE STATE.
ALL THAT RAIN WASHING AWAY
ROADS.
THIS IS WHAT'S LEFT OF STATE
ROUTE 66.
IN SOUTHEAST MISSOURI, HOWLING
WIND GUSTS KNOCKING THIS TRAIN
OFF ITS TRACKS.
TORNADOES REPORTED IN SEVERAL
STATES.
MEANWHILE, IN THE NORTHERN
PLAINS, BLIZZARD CONDITIONS UP
TO A FOOT OF SNOW CLOSING
INTERSTATES.
VISIBILITY SO POOR IN ST. CLOUD,
MINNESOTA, THIS STORMCHASER
NEARLY SLAMMING INTO A TRACTOR
TRAILER.
>> WHOA!
>> Reporter: IN THE MIDWEST, UP
TO HALF AN INCH OF ICE COATING
ROADS, TREES AND POWER LINES,
THREATENING TO KNOCK OUT POWER
TO THOUSANDS.
IN OVERLAND PARK, KANSAS, A HIGH
SCHOOL PRINCIPAL TAKING A TUMBLE
OUT OF HIS TRUCK.
HE POSTED THE VIDEO WITH A
LAUGH, BUT THE ICE, NO JOKE.
IN ILLINOIS, A BRIEF THAW
CAUSING MAJOR ICE JAMS ALONG A
FROZEN KANKAKEE RIVER.
HOMEOWNERS LIKE JOJO BROADWELL,
WHO LIVE ALONG THE RIVER,
BRACING FOR THE WORST.
>> IT'S LIKE A BULLDOZER COMING
UP.
THERE'S NOTHING STOPPING THIS
ICE.
IT WILL DESTROY ANYTHING IN ITS
PATH.
>> AND DAVID, I WANT TO SHOW YOU
WHY THERE IS SO MUCH CONCERN
HERE.
THERE IS A HOME RIGHT HERE.
AND IF WALK WITH ME, 20 FEET
AWAY, THERE'S A GROWING ICEBERG
SLOWLY CREEPING INTO THE
BACKYARD HERE.
LUCKILY, OFFICIALS SAY, THE
RIVER IS NOW MOVING AND THE
WATER IS RECEDING.
DAVID?
>> ALEX, THANK YOU.
LET'S GET RIGHT TO ROB MARCIANO,
LIVE WITH US TONIGHT, TRACKING
IT ALL AS THIS MOVES EAST.
HI, ROB.
>> Reporter: HI, DAVID.
THIS STORM HAS REALLY STRETCHED
OUT.
WE HAD FOUR STATES REPORTING
TORNADOES, NOT TO MENTION THE
FLOODING AND THE SNOW.
BLIZZARD WARNINGS UP FOR
MINNESOTA AND THE FLASH FLOOD
WATCHES FOR NEARLY ALL OF OHIO.
HERE COMES THE HEAVY RAIN.
GOING TO BE IN THE NORTHEAST FOR
THE MORNING RUSH, WITH A LITTLE
BIT OF MIXING OF WINTER
PRECIPITATION.
AND MUCH COLDER.
WE SNAP BACK TO WINTER.
30 BELOW IN MINNEAPOLIS TOMORROW
FOR A MORNING WIND CHILL AND
ANOTHER WINTER STORM COMING FOR
SEATTLE.
SIGNIFICANT SNOW EVENT BEGINNING
THERE TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
DAVID?
>> ROB MARCIANO TRACKING IT FOR
US.
THANK YOU, ROB.
>>> WE'RE GOING TO TURN NEXT TO
THE POLITICAL CRISIS IN
VIRGINIA, AND IN AN UNBELIEVABLE
TURN, GROWING YET AGAIN TONIGHT.
FIRST, IT WAS THE GOVERNOR UNDER
PRESSURE TO RESIGN FOR THAT
RACIST IMAGE IN HIS MEDICAL
SCHOOL YEARBOOK, THEN THE
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR, WHO WOULD
SERVE NEXT, HE'S FACING THAT
ALLEGATION OF SEXUAL ASSAULT,
FOLLOWED BY THE STATE ATTORNEY
GENERAL, REVEALING HE WORE
BLACKFACE ONCE IN COLLEGE.
ALL THREE DEMOCRATS.
AND NOW, TONIGHT, ANOTHER TOP
LAWMAKER, A REPUBLICAN, FACING
QUESTIONS ABOUT HIS PAST.
ABC'S CHIEF NATIONAL AFFAIRS
CORRESPONDENT TOM LLAMAS FROM
RICHMOND, THE STATE CAPITAL.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT IN
VIRGINIA, GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM
HAS ALL BUT VANISHED.
NO WORD FROM HIM AT ALL IN A
NEARLY A WEEK.
AN AVALANCHE OF HEADLINES
TELLING THE TALE, "STATE OF
TURMOIL," "POLITICAL CRISIS
ESCALATES," "WHAT NEXT?"
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR, HOW ARE YOU
DOING?
TOM LLAMAS FROM ABC NEWS.
VIRGINIA'S SECOND
HIGHEST RANKING ELECTED
OFFICIAL, LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR
JUSTIN FAIRFAX, NOW FENDING OFF
AN ALLEGATION OF SEXUAL ASSAULT.
DR. VANESSA TYSON ALLEGING HE
FORCED HER TO PERFORM ORAL SEX
IN A HOTEL ROOM AT THE
2004 DEMOCRATIC NATIONAL
CONVENTION.
FAIRFAX SAYS THEIR ENCOUNTER WAS
CONSENSUAL.
DO YOU REMEMBER DR. TYSON EVER
CRYING?
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU, MAN.
>> Reporter: DO YOU REMEMBER
DR. TYSON EVER CRYING?
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU GUYS.
WE'RE HEADING TO SESSION.
>> Reporter: NOW, SOME NATIONAL
DEMOCRATS, EVEN THOUGH RUNNING
FOR PRESIDENT, CALLING FOR AN
INVESTIGATION.
>> THE LETTER WRITTEN BY THE
WOMAN READS AS A CREDIBLE
ACCOUNT.
>> Reporter: THE STATE'S
THIRD-HIGHEST RANKING OFFICIAL,
ATTORNEY GENERAL MARK HERRING,
ANOTHER DEMOCRAT, ALSO ENGULFED
IN SCANDAL AFTER ADMITTING HE,
TOO, WORE BLACKFACE ONCE IN THE
1980s.
AND NOW, A FOURTH TOP OFFICIAL
COMING UNDER FIRE, AS WELL.
THIS TIME, A REPUBLICAN.
THE VIRGINIA PILOT NEWSPAPER
REPORTING THAT SENATE MAJORITY
LEADER THOMAS NORMAN WAS
MANAGING EDITOR OF THE 1968
YEARBOOK OF THE VIRGINIA
MILITARY INSTITUTE, WHICH
FEATURED SEVERAL STUDENTS IN
BLACKFACE AND CONTAINED RACIAL
SLURS.
SENATOR, DO YOU REGRET WHAT'S IN
THE YEARBOOK?
DO YOU REGRET IT?
DO YOU APOLOGIZE AT ALL?
>> I'M HERE TO TALK ABOUT THE
BUDGET.
>> Reporter: THE SENATOR LATER
SAYING HE WAS NOT IN ANY OF
THOSE PHOTOS AND HE ADVOCATED
FOR RACIAL INTEGRATION WHILE AT
VMI.
IS THERE ANYTHING WE CAN ALL
LEARN FROM WHAT'S HAPPENED HERE
IN VIRGINIA THE LAST FEW DAYS?
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
ANYTHING THAT WE ALL CAN LEARN,
BUT I WILL SAY THAT PROBABLY IN
THE NEWS MEDIA, YOU'RE SMARTER
WHEN YOU LOOK IN THE REARVIEW
MIRROR.
>> TOM LLAMAS WITH US TONIGHT
FROM THE STATE CAPITAL IN
RICHMOND, VIRGINIA.
AND TOM, WORD TONIGHT THAT THE
GOVERNOR, GOVERNOR NORTHAM, HAS
REACHED OUT TO THE LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
AFTER DAYS OF NO COMMUNICATION,
THE GOVERNOR AND THE LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR SPOKE THIS MORNING.
WE UNDERSTAND THAT CONVERSATION
WITH CORDIAL.
BOTH MEN WISHED EACH OTHER WELL.
AND AT ONE POINT, THEY BOTH SAID
THEY WERE PRAYING FOR EACH
OTHER.
DAVID?
>> TOM LLAMAS AGAIN TONIGHT.
THANK YOU, TOM.
>>> THIS EVENING, THE MANHUNT
FOR A KILLER IN TEXAS IS UNDER
WAY, AFTER A WOMAN WAS KILLED
WHILE SETTING UP A GARAGE SALE.
SURVEILLANCE SHOWING THE GUNMAN
APPROACHING THE WOMAN IN HER
DRIVEWAY, EXCHANGING SOME WORDS
AND THEN FIRING POINT BLANK.
TONIGHT, POLICE ARE NOW ASKING
FOR THE PUBLIC'S HELP, AND ABC'S
MARCUS MOORE IS ON THE SCENE.
>> Reporter: THIS TERRIFYING
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO SHOWING
ELIZABETH BARRAZA'S
EXECUTION-STYLE MURDER HAS
INVESTIGATORS OUTSIDE OF HOUSTON
PUZZLED.
JUST FOUR MINUTES AFTER HER
HUSBAND LEFT FOR WORK, THE
29-YEAR-OLD WAS MURDERED WHILE
SETTING UP A GARAGE SALE IN HER
OWN DRIVEWAY.
THAT SUSPECT, SHOOTING BARRAZA
FOUR TIMES AT POINT BLANK RANGE
EARLY IN THE MORNING ON
JON 25th, THEN RUNNING AWAY ON
FOOT BEFORE DRIVING OFF IN THIS
DARK-COLORED TRUCK.
POLICE SAY IT'S UNCLEAR WHETHER
BARRAZA WAS TARGETED.
SHE HAD ONLY PUT OUT SIGNS FOR
THAT GARAGE SALE THAT MORNING.
AND INVESTIGATORS DON'T EVEN
KNOW IF THE SHOOTER IS A MAN OR
A WOMAN.
>> DEFINITELY IT IS POSSIBLE
THEY WERE TRYING TO DISGUISE
THEIR APPEARANCE.
>> Reporter: HER FAMILY MAKING A
PLEA FOR THE PUBLIC TO HELP FIND
THE KILLER.
>> WE HAD TO TRADE OUR FIFTH
ANNIVERSARY FOR HER FUNERAL.
>> Reporter: AND DAVID, THIS
GARAGE SALE IN THE DRIVEWAY HERE
WAS TO RAISE MONEY FOR AN
ANNIVERSARY TRIP WITH HER
HUSBAND.
AUTHORITIES SAY THEY HAVE
GENERATED NEW LEADS OVERNIGHT,
BUT THIS CASE REMAINS A MYSTERY.
DAVID?
>> ALL RIGHT, MARCUS, THANK YOU.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP TONIGHT IS
LASHING OUT, AS DEMOCRATS WHO
NOW CONTROL THE HOUSE HAVE
STEPPED UP THEIR OVERSIGHT.
THE PRESIDENT CALLING IT, QUOTE,
PRESIDENTIAL HARASSMENT, SAYING
THE DEMS ARE, QUOTE, GOING NUTS.
HOUSE SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI
PUSHING BACK TONIGHT, CALLING
THE SCRUTINY ON THE PRESIDENT
THEIR CONSTITUTIONAL SPOT, AND
TONIGHT, ONE TARGET?
THE PRESIDENT'S TAXES.
ABC'S MARY BRUCE UP ON THE HILL.
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS IN
CONGRESS ARE KICKING THEIR
INVESTIGATIONS OF THE TRUMP
PRESIDENCY INTO HIGH GEAR.
>> I THINK OVERWHELMINGLY THE
PUBLIC WANTS TO SEE THE
PRESIDENT'S TAX RETURNS.
>> Reporter: UNLIKE PREVIOUS
PRESIDENTS, TRUMP HAS REFUSED TO
RELEASE HIS RETURNS.
>> I'M NOT RELEASING THE TAX
RETURNS, BECAUSES YOU KNOW,
THEY'RE UNDER AUDIT.
>> Reporter: BUT NOW, DEMOCRATS
HAVE THE POWER TO GO AFTER THEM.
>> WE WILL ASK THE QUESTION,
DOES THE PUBLIC HAVE A NEED TO
KNOW THAT A PERSON SEEKING TO
HOLD THE HIGHEST OFFICE IN OUR
COUNTRY OBEYS THE TAX LAW?
>> Reporter: WITH DEMOCRATS
DIGGING IN, THE PRESIDENT IS
LASHING OUT, TWEETING,
"UNLIMITED PRESIDENTIAL
HARASSMENT.
THE DEMS AND THEIR COMMITTEES
ARE GOING NUTS."
IS THERE ANY CONCERN THAT YOU'RE
IN DANGER OF APPEARING LIKE
YOU'RE OVERREACHING?
>> WHATEVER THE PRESIDENT SAYS
ABOUT US, HE'S PROJECTING HIS
OWN UNRULINESS.
HE'S A PROJECTOR, AND THAT'S
WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
>> Reporter: THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE IS
LAUNCHING A SWEEPING
INVESTIGATION INTO THE
PRESIDENT, HIS FAMILY, HIS
FINANCES AND POSSIBLE RUSSIA
TIES.
AND TONIGHT, A STANDOFF BETWEEN
THE HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE
AND THE PRESIDENT'S ACTING
ATTORNEY GENERAL, MATTHEW
WHITAKER.
COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN GERALD NADLER
THREATENED TO SUBPOENA WHITAKER
IF HE DOESN'T SHOW UP AT A
SCHEDULED HEARING TOMORROW.
WHITAKER THEN REFUSING TO APPEAR
UNLESS THE CONGRESSMAN DROPS
THAT THREAT.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO, LET'S GET TO
MARY BRUCE LIVE, BECAUSE THERE
ARE FAST-MOVING PARTS ON THIS
STORY TONIGHT.
JUST MOMENTS AGO, MARY, THE
WHITE HOUSE RELEASING A
STATEMENT ABOUT THE ACTING
ATTORNEY GENERAL?
>> Reporter: YES, AND DAVID, THE
CHAIRMAN HERE STILL ISN'T RULING
OUT THAT SUBPOENA, SAYING IT
DEPENDS ON HOW WHITAKER ANSWERS
THEIR QUESTIONS, IF HE SHOWS UP
HERE TOMORROW.
BUT TONIGHT, THE WHITE HOUSE
SAYS THE CHAIRMAN IS, QUOTE,
PLAYING POINTLESS POLITICAL
GAMES.
DAVID?
>> MARY BRUCE, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW, TO AN ABC NEWS
EXCLUSIVE TONIGHT, IN THE CASE
OF JAYME CLOSS.
THE FATHER OF HER ACCUSED
KIDNAPPER IS NOW BREAKING HIS
SILENCE.
HIS SON, JAKE PATTERSON, IS
ACCUSED OF HOLDING KLOSS CAPTIVE
FOR 88 DAYS AFTER KILLING HER
PARENTS.
TONIGHT, HIS FATHER, WHO
ACTUALLY VISITED THAT HOME, NOT
KNOWING CLOSS WAS THERE.
HERE'S ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS.
>> Reporter: JAKE PATTERSON IS
ACCUSED OF ABDUCTING JAYME CLOSS
AND KILLING HER PARENTS, AND NOW
HIS FATHER IS SPEAKING
EXCLUSIVELY TO ABC NEWS.
>> I MOST DEFINITELY WANT
JAYME'S FAMILY, EVERYONE, TO
KNOW THAT OUR HEARTS ARE BROKEN
FOR THEIR FAMILY.
>> Reporter: ON WEDNESDAY,
PATTERSON MADE HIS FIRST COURT
APPEARANCE.
>> AND DO YOU UNDERSTAND THE
CHARGES AGAINST YOU AT THIS
TIME?
>> YES.
>> Reporter: PATRICK PATTERSON
IS STILL STRUGGLING TO MAKE
SENSE OF IT ALL.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO HUMBLY ASK
PEOPLE TO PRAY FOR A COMPLETE
HEALING OF JAYME'S HEART, MIND
AND SOUL.
>> Reporter: PATTERSON ALLEGEDLY
TARGETED THE 13-YEAR-OLD AFTER
SEEING HER BOARD A SCHOOL BUS IN
OCTOBER, TELLING POLICE, "HE
KNEW THAT WAS THE GIRL HE WAS
GOING TO TAKE."
HE'S ACCUSED OF KILLING JAYME'S
PARENTS IN A HOME INVASION AND
HOLDING HER CAPTIVE FOR 88 DAYS
AT HIS HOME WHERE, SHE SAYS, HE
BARRICADED HER UNDER HIS BED FOR
12 HOURS AT A TIME UNTIL SHE
ESCAPED.
>> I'M VERY SORRY FOR EVERYTHING
THAT HAS HAPPENED.
>> Reporter: PATTERSON ALLEGEDLY
CONFESSED THAT THERE WERE
MULTIPLE TIMES WHEN HIS FATHER
WOULD COME OVER AND WAS JUST
FEET AWAY FROM JAYME AND HAD NO
IDEA, BECAUSE SHE WAS BARRICADED
UNDER THE BED WITH THE RADIO
TURNED UP.
DAVID?
>> WOW.
ALL RIGHT, LINSEY DAVIS WITH THE
EXCLUSIVE TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS THURSDAY.
CELEBRATING A BASEBALL LEGEND
TONIGHT.
A TRUE TRAIL BLAZER.
>>> ALSO, THE HORRIFIC CASE OF
APPARENT ROAD RAGE.
NEW IMAGES TONIGHT, THE DRIVER
OPENING FIRE ON A SCHOOL BUS,
HITTING THE DRIVER TWICE.
THERE WAS A YOUNG STUDENT
ONBOARD.
>>> THE MURDER HISTORY OUTSIDE
NEW YORK CITY TONIGHT.
THE WOMAN'S BODICE COVERED IN A
SUITCASE, AND THIS EVENING, WHAT
WE'VE NOW LEARNED ABOUT HER
IDENTITY.
>>> AND THE STUNNING IMAGE THIS
EVENING.
THE YOUNG GIRL SAVED AFTER 18
HOURS BURIED UNDER THE RUBBLE OF
A COLLAPSED BUILDING.
YOU WILL SEE THE MOMENT SHE IS
RUSHED TO SAFETY.
A LOT MORE NEWS AHEAD TONIGHT.
d:
When it comes to managing
your type 2 diabetes,
what matters to you?
Let's see.
Most of you say lower A1C.
But only a few of you
are thinking about your heart.
Fact is, even though
it helps to manage A1C,
type 2 diabetes still
increases your risk
of a fatal heart
attack or stroke.
JARDIANCE is the first
type 2 diabetes pill
with a lifesaving
cardiovascular benefit
for adults who have type 2
diabetes and heart disease,
JARDIANCE significantly
reduces the risk of dying
from a cardiovascular event
and lowers A1C,
with diet and exercise.
Let's give it another try.
JARDIANCE can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration.
This may cause you
to feel dizzy, faint,
or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis
is a serious side effect
that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting, stomach pain,
tiredness,
and trouble breathing.
A rare but life-threatening
bacterial infection
in the skin of the genital
area could also occur.
Stop taking JARDIANCE
and call your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of this bacterial infection,
ketoacidosis
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic
reaction include rash,
swelling, and difficulty
breathing or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects are
sudden kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about
all the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
Isn't it time to rethink your
type 2 diabetes medication?
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE
and get to the heart
of what matters.
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE
98% of us don't get enough
omega-3s.
Which is why MegaRed Advanced
4in1
packs more omega-3 power into
one small softgel.
It supports your heart...
Brain... Eyes... And joints.
MegaRed.
>>> WE'RE GOING TO TURN NOW TO
THAT APPARENT ROAD RAGE SHOOTING
IN MINNEAPOLIS.
A DRIVER SHOOTING A SCHOOL BUS
DRIVER AND HITTING THE BUS
DRIVER TWICE.
HERE'S ABC'S CLAYTON SANDELL
WITH THE NEW SURVEILLANCE.
>> Reporter: WHAT POLICE SAY
STARTED AS A FENDER BENDER
BETWEEN A CAR AND A SCHOOL BUS,
TONIGHT, A CASE OF ATTEMPTED
MURDER.
CAPTURED TUESDAY ON THIS
MINNEAPOLIS TRAFFIC CAMERA,
POLICE SAY THIS IS 31-YEAR-OLD
KENNETH LILLY, STOPPED IN
TRAFFIC, WALKING TOWARDS THE BUS
AFTER IT APPARENTLY BUMPED HIS
CAR.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE THE GUY IS IN
SOME SORT OF SECURITY UNIFORM OR
SOMETHING.
LOOKS LIKE HE IS -- DOES HAVE A
WEAPON ON HIM.
>> Reporter: WHEN THE BUS DRIVER
REFUSES TO LET LILLY ONBOARD
BECAUSE THERE'S AN 8-YEAR-OLD
GIRL IN THE BACK, POLICE SAY
LILLY PULLS A .9 MILLIMETER
HANDGUN, AND YOU CAN SEE THE
FLASHES, OPENS FIRE, STRIKING
THE BUS DRIVER IN THE ARM AND
GRAZING HIS HEAD.
>> PULLED OVER ON THE LEFT
SHOULDER, I'VE GOT HIM ON
CAMERA.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY LILLY
THEN CALLS 911.
OFFICERS ARRIVING MOMENTS LATER
AND TAKE HIM INTO CUSTODY.
INVESTIGATORS SAY LILLY TOLD
THEM HE FEARED FOR HIS LIFE.
BUT PROSECUTORS SAY THE VIDEO
SHOWS HE WAS IN NO DANGER.
>> WE DO NOT BELIEVE THERE WAS A
SELF DEFENSE CLAIM BASED UPON
THE EVIDENCE WE HAVE RECEIVED SO
FAR.
>> Reporter: LILLY IS CHARGED
WITH ATTEMPTED MURDER AND
ASSAULT.
THE BUS DRIVER, EXPECTED TO BE
OKAY AND HIS 8-YEAR-OLD
PASSENGER WAS NOT HURT.
DAVID?
>> THANK YOU, CLAYTON.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, A WOMAN
DISCOVERED IN A SUITCASE IN NEW
YORK.
>>> AND TOMORROW, WHAT'S COMING
UP ON "20/20."
A STORY WE'VE COVERED FOR YEARS.
>>> A MOTHER, A WIFE, HER FIRST
HUSBAND, DEKD.
HER SECOND HUSBAND, DEAD.
THEN, HER DAUGHTER POISONS.
NOW, NEW DETAILS, AND THE DAVID
MUIR PRISON INTERVIEW THAT MADE
HEADLINES.
>> STACY CASTER IS CONVICTED OF
MURDERING HER HUSBAND, CONVICTED
OF ATTEMPTED MURDER OF HER OWN
DAUGHTER.
AND SHE'S WALKING TOWARDS US AND
WE WONDER, WHAT IS SHE GOING TO
SAY THIS TIME?
>> THE "20/20" EVENT, FRIDAY ON
ABC.
family and FARXIGA,
the pill that starts with "f."
FARXIGA, along with
diet and exercise,
helps lower A1C in adults
with type 2 diabetes.
It's one pill a day.
And although it's not a
weight-loss drug,
it may help you lose weight.
Do not take if
allergic to FARXIGA.
If you experience symptoms
of a serious allergic reaction
such as rash, swelling,
difficulty breathing
or swallowing,
stop taking and seek
medical help right away.
Do not take FARXIGA if you
have severe kidney problems,
are on dialysis or
have bladder cancer.
Tell your doctor right
away if you have blood
or red color in your urine
or pain while you urinate.
FARXIGA can cause serious side
effects including dehydration,
genital yeast infections
in women and men,
serious urinary
tract infections,
low blood sugar,
and kidney problems.
Stop taking FARXIGA and
call your doctor right away
if you have signs
of ketoacidosis
which is serious and
may lead to death.
Ask your doctor about the pill
that starts with "f"
and visit FARXIGA.com
for savings.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may be
able to help.
If you can't afford
your medication,
Hey, Darryl!
Hey, Thomas.
If you were choosing a network,
would you want the one
the experts at
RootMetrics say
is number one
in the nation?
Sure, they probably know
what they're talking about.
Or the one
that J.D. Power says
is highest in
network quality
by people
who use it every day?
This is a tough one.
Well, not really,
because Verizon won both.
So you don't even
have to choose.
Why didn't you just
lead with that?
It's like a fun thing.
(VO)
Chosen by experts.
Chosen by you.
Get 50 million songs now
with Apple Music included,
on us.
On both iOS and Android.
It's the unlimited plan you need
on the network you deserve.
I work hard to protect
this Tookus.
To take care of any
messy situations.
And put irritation in its place.
And if I can get comfortable
keeping this Tookus
safe and protected...
you can get comfortable doing
the same with yours.
PREPARATION H.
Get comfortable with it.
Oh, wow. You two are going to
have such a great trip.
Thanks to you, we will.
This is why Voya helps reach
today's goals...
all while helping you to and
through retirement.
Can you help with these?
We're more of the plan, invest
and protect kind of help...
Voya. Helping you to and through
retirement.
Woman:
This is your wake-up call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis,
month after month,
the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
HUMIRA can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
HUMIRA targets and blocks
a source of inflammation
that contributes
to joint pain
and irreversible damage.
VO: HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections
including tuberculosis,
and cancers, including
lymphoma, have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Woman:
Help stop the clock
on further irreversible
joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here. Right now.
HUMIRA.
>>> TO THE INDEX, AND TO THE
MURDER MYSTERY IN CONNECTICUT.
POLICE NOW IDENTIFYING THE
VICTIM.
VALERIE RACE WAS FOUND STUFFED
IN A SUITCASE ON THE SIDE OF THE
ROAD.
SHE WAS REPORTED MISSING FROM
NEW YORK A WEEK AGO WHEN SHE
FAILED TO SHOW UP AT WORK.
HER MOTHER SAYS HER DAUGHTER
FEARED FOR HER OWN SAFETY BEFORE
SHE VANISHED, AND POLICE ARE
STILL SEARCHING FOR THE KILLER
TONIGHT.
>>> AND THE IMAGE OVERSEAS THIS
EVENING, THE AMAZING RESCUE IN
TURKEY.
A 5-YEAR-OLD GIRL PULLED ALIVE
FROM THE RUBBLE.
18 HOURS AFTER AN EIGHT-STORY
BUILDING COLLAPSED IN ISTANBUL.
AT LEAST TEN PEOPLE WERE KILLED.
RESCUERS BELIEVE THERE MAY BE
MORE SURVIVORS STILL.
THE CAUSE IS STILL UNDER
INVESTIGATION.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK TONIGHT,
CELEBRATING A BASEBALL LEGEND.
A TRAIL BLAZER.
AND WHAT WE UNEARTHED TODAY, IN
A MOMENT.
If you have postmenopausal
osteoporosis
and a high risk for fracture
now might not be the best time
to ask yourself
are my bones strong?
Life is full of make-or-break
moments.
That's why it's so important
to help reduce your risk of
fracture with Prolia®.
Only Prolia® is proven to help
strengthen
and protect bones from fracture
with 1 shot every 6 months.
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take
XGEVA®.
Serious allergic reactions,
like low blood pressure; trouble
breathing;
throat tightness; face, lip, or
tongue swelling;
rash; itching; or hives have
happened.
Tell your doctor about dental
problems
as severe jaw bone problems may
happen
or new or unusual pain in your
hip groin, or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone fractures
have occurred.
Speak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects,
like low blood calcium, serious
infections,
which could need
hospitalization, skin problems,
and severe bone, joint, or
muscle pain.
Are you ready?
Ask your doctor how Prolia® can
help strengthen your bones.
Gentle means everything,
so we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients
Added one handed pumps
And beat the
top safety standards
The new JOHNSON'S®
Choose Gentle
Building a better bank
starts with looking
at something old,
and saying, "really?"
So Capital One is building
something completely new.
Capital One Cafes.
Inviting places with
people here to help you,
not sell you.
And savings and
checking accounts with
no fees or minimums.
Because that's
how it should be.
You can open one from
right here or anywhere
in 5 minutes.
Seriously,
5 minutes...
This is Banking Reimagined.
What's in your wallet?
Ok look, if you're not
the lead dog,
the scenery never changes.
That's why this is the view
for every other full-size
pickup.
And this year,
it's déjà vu all over again
'Cuz only the Ford F-150 with
its high strength,
military-grade
aluminum alloy body
gives you best-in-class torque,
best-in-class payload...
and you got it, baby...
best-in-class towing.
Still leading the pack.
This is the big dog!
This is the Ford F-150.
It doesn't just
raise the bar, pal.
It is the bar.
Colon cancer screening
for people
50 and older at average risk.
I think it's time
for a new screen.
For a different
kind of screen...
for colon cancer.
Thought about it?
His wife asked
about screening options
and her doctor
ordered me.
I'm Cologuard,
the noninvasive
test you use at home.
No special drink.
Just a trip
to the bathroom!
Cologuard.
Colon cancer screening
that's as easy as get,
go, gone.
Cologuard is not
right for everyone,
so ask your doctor if
it's right for you.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, AMERICA
STRONG.
CELEBRATING LEGENDARY HALL OF
FAMER FRANK ROBINSON, MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL'S FIRST
AFRICAN-AMERICAN MANAGER, AND
ONE OF THE GAME'S GREATEST
STARS.
>> LINE DRIVE TO LEFT FIELD.
WAY BACK -- IT IS GONE!
>> PROBABLY ONE OF THE TOP FIVE
TOUGHEST PLAYERS THAT I'VE EVER
BEEN AROUND.
THIS GUY WAS NOT ONLY A GREAT
PLAYER, HE WAS A HARD PLAYER,
BOY.
HE WAS AS TOUGH AS NAILS.
>> Reporter: FRANK ROBINSON WAS
ONE OF BASEBALL'S MOST
CELEBRATED AND MOST
INTIMIDATING HITTERS.
STARTING WITH THE REDS IN 1956,
HE WAS ROOKIE OF THE YEAR.
>> HE WAS THE BEST THAT I HAVE
EVER SEEN AT KNOWING WHAT THE
PITCHER WAS THROWING.
FRANK COULD TAKE HIS HAT OFF,
PUT IT IN FRONT OF HIS FACE AND
LOOK THROUGH ONE OF THOSE LITTLE
HOLES IN HIS HAT AND I ASKED HIM
ONE TIME, WHAT YOU ARE DOING?
AND HE SAID, I'M WATCHING THE
PITCHER.
>> Reporter: THEN ROBINSON'S
FIRST YEAR WITH THE ORIOLES,
1966, WOULD HELP CEMENT HIS
PLACE AS ONE OF THE GREATEST
BASEBALL PLAYERS OF ALL TIME.
HE WON BASEBALL'S TRIPLE CROWN,
LEADING THE LEAGUE WITH
49 HOMERS.
EARNING THE AMERICAN LEAGUE MVP
AWARD AND LEADING THE ORIOLES TO
THEIR FIRST WORLD SERIES TITLE.
>> ROBINSON, THE RIGHT-HAND
BATTER.
LONG DRIVE TO LEFT FIELD.
WAY BACK, WAY BACK.
KISS IT GOODBYE.
HOMERUN.
>> Reporter: HE WOULD LATER MAKE
HISTORY AS A MANAGER.
NO AFRICAN-AMERICAN HAD EVER
MANAGED IN THE MAJOR LEAGUES.
LEADING THE CLEVELAND INDIANS
STARTING IN 1975.
>> EVERYWHERE I WENT IT WAS,
HOW'S IT FEEL TO BE THE FIRST
BLACK MANAGER?
I JUST WANTED TO BE LOOKED UP ON
AND THOUGHT OF AS A MAJOR LEAGUE
MANAGER.
PEOPLE MADE SACRIFICES FOR ME,
COMING ALONG, SO, I WANTED TO
GIVE SOMETHING BACK AND THE DAY
THAT I FEEL LIKE I HAVE NOTHING
TO GIVE, OR NOTHING TO OFFER
BASEBALL, THAT'S WHEN I WILL
THEN FADE OFF INTO THE SUNSET.
>> A TRUE LEGEND.
ROBINSON WAS 83.
OUR THANKS TO ESPN AS WE LOOK
BACK TODAY.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
GOOD NIGHT.
NIGHT.
Everyone's got to listen to mom.
When it comes to reducing the
sugar in your family's diet,
Coke, Dr Pepper and Pepsi hear
you.
We're working together to do
just that.
Bringing you more great tasting
beverages with less sugar
or no sugar at all.
Smaller portion sizes,
clear calorie labels and
reminders to think balance.
Because we know mom wants what's
best.
More beverage choices, smaller
portions, less sugar.
BalanceUS.org
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
[ MUSIC PLAYING ]
>>> HELLO, EVERYONE, WELCOME TO
"AMANPOUR AND COMPANY."
HERE'S WHAT'S COMING UP.
>> TREMENDOUS NUMBERS DON'T LIE
>> THE PRESIDENT AND THE
POTENTIAL 2020 RIVALS TAKE TO
TEXAS.
THOUSANDS OF MILES AWAY,
CONGRESS APPEARS TO COMPROMISE
ON THE KEEPING THE GOVERNMENT
OPENED.
WE GET THE BORDER STORY FROM THE
REPUBLICAN MAYOR OF EL PASO AND
THE HUMANITARIAN FACE OF
IMMIGRATION FROM THOSE CLOSEST
TO HIM.
>>> PLUS, FEARS OF BIG BROTHER
THE FORMER HOMELAND SECURITY ON
THE DANGERS OF GOVERNMENT UNDER
SURVEILLANCE FROM CHINA TO
AMERICA.
WHEN BAE COLEMAN'S CAREER BEGAN,
SHE DIDN'T NOW KNOW HER COOKBOOK
WOULD MAKE IT TO UNIWORLD.
HER CUISINE IS SERVED THROUGH
EUROPE, ASIA, INDIA AND EUROPE,
ACCORDING TO BAE, TO TRAVEL IS
TO EAT.
>>> WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM,
EVERYONE, I'M CHRISTIANE
AMANPOUR IN LONDON.
PRSIDENT TRUMP SAYS HE'S NOT
SATISFIED WITH THE CONGRESSIONAL
BREAK THROUGH TO KEEP THE
GOVERNMENT OPENED.
HOUSE AND SENATE LEADERS ARE
GIVING THE PRESIDENT SOME FUNDS
FOR BORDER BARRIERS, NOT THE
$5.7 BILLION HE IS DEMANDING.
SPEAKING IN THE CABINET ROOM HE
SAID HE DIDN'T EXPECT ANOTHER
SHUTDOWN, ALSO HE SAID THIS.
>> SO I CAN TELL YOU AM I HAPPY
AT FIRST GLANCE?
I JUST GOT TO SEE IT.
THE ANSWER IS, NO, I'M NOT.
I'M NOT HAPPY.
BUT AM I HAPPY WITH WHERE WE'RE
GOING?
I'LL THRILLED.
BECAUSE WE ARE SUPPLEMENTING
THINGS AND MOVING THINGS AROUND
AND WE'RE DOING THINGS THAT ARE
FANTASTIC AND TAKING FROM FAR
LESS REALLY FROM FAR LESS
IMPORTANT AREAS.
>> SO WHILE NEGOTIATORS WERE
WORKING ON THE DEAL IN
WASHINGTON.
THE PRESIDENT WAS IN EL PASO,
TEXAS LAST NIGHT ON THE BODER
RALLYING HIS WALL-LOVING BASE.
HE ALSO HAD ONE EYE ON THE
DEMOCRATS BETO O'ROURKE.
HE RAN FOR SENATE IN 2018 AND
MIGHT RUN FOR PRESIDENT IN 2020.
AS A CONGRESSMAN, HE REPRESENTED
EMPASS SO.
>> THE PRESIDENT DESCRIBES
MEXICAN IMMIGRANTS AS RAPISTS
AND CRIMINALS.
WE HAVE THE CHANCE TO TELL HIM
AND THE COUNTRY, IMMIGRANTS
COMMIT CRIMES, INCLUDING VIOLENT
CRIMES AT A LOWER RATE THAN DO
AMERICANS WHO WERE BORN IN THIS
COUNTRY EL PASO HAS BEEN THE
SAFEST CITY IN THE UNITED STATES
OF AMERICA, NOT INSPITE OF THE
FACT THAT WE ARE A CITY OF
IMMIGRANTS, BUT BECAUSE WE ARE A
CITY OF IMMIGRANTS.
>> EL PASO HAS BECOME A
TOUCHDOWN OF WALL POLITICS.
THE CITY OF MORE THAN 50 MILES
OF FENCING ALONG THE BORDER.
SO WHAT IS THE PROBLEM THERE,
THE MAYOR JOINS ME NOW.
MAYOR, WELL DOCK BA TO THE
PROGRAM.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT EL PASO WOULD HAVE BEEN
A TOUCHSTONE AS I SAID IN THIS
WHOLE POLITICAL DRAMA.
BEFORE WE GET TO THAT, CAN I ASK
YOU ABOUT THE NEWS, WHAT YOU
THINK ABOUT THE COMPROMISE DEAL
BEING ON BOARD SECURITY TO TRY
TO KEEP THE GOVERNMENT OPENED
AND AFLOAT?
>> I HAVEN'T REALLY SEEN
ANYTHING IN THE HEADLINES ON THE
NEWS ABOUT IT.
I DON'T KNOW ANY OF THE
SPECIFICS.
I'M PROBABLY NOT ALLOWED TO
COMMENT.
FROM MY TIME IN THE LEGISLATURE
I WOULD SAY INCREMENT AM MOVING
UP INCREMENTALLY IS THE WAY TO
DO IT.
ON THE EL PASO PORTRAYERS, THERE
WERE NO WINNERS.
>> YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
WE SPENT MANY OF THOSE 35 DAYS
OF GOVERNMENT CLOSURE TALKING TO
SO MANY PEOPLE, FURLOUGHED
FEDERAL WORKERS.
SO MANY PEOPLE WHO HAD SUCH A
HARD TIME GETTING THROUGH AND
SURVIVING THIS SHUTDOWN.
I GUESS YOU ARE SITTING THERE AT
THE NEXUS OF THE GREAT POLITICAL
DRAMA OF OUR TIME.
SO WHEN YOU HAD THE PRESIDENT
AND A POTENTIAL 2020 RIVAL THERE
RALLYING LAST NIGHT.
WHAT DID YOU HEAR?
WHAT DID YOU TAKE AWAY FROM
EVERYTHING THAT WAS SAID?
>> I'M NOT SURE THERE WERE ANY
REVELATIONS FROM THE COMMENTS OF
EITHER BETO OR THE PRESIDENT.
I WAS TRYING TO PERSONALLY MEET
WITH THE PRESIDENT BEFOREHAND TO
VISIT WITH HIM.
BECAUSE I'VE SAID FOR MONTHS
THAT IF YOU WANT TO UNDERSTAND
THE BORDER, AND HOW YOU WORK
WITH MEXICO, YOU NEED TO COME TO
THE LARGEST CITY ON THE MEXICO
BORDER THAT HAS BEEN INTERTWINED
FOR ALMOST 400 YEARS, WE
UNDERSTAND IT BETTER, WE'RE THE
PLACE YOU OUGHT TO BE COMING TO
TALK ABOUT IT.
>> AND YET, DID YOU ACTUALLY MAN
TO SAY THAT TO HIM?
DID YOU MEET HIM?
>> I GOT A HANDSHAKE.
THAT WAS THE EXTENT OF IT.
WE THOUGHT WE WOULD GET MORE
TIME.
THAT WAS TRULY THE EXTENT OF IT.
>> DIFEEL HE WAS NOT TRYING TO
MEET YOU.
HE KNOWS YOU DISAGREE, HAVE YOU
DIFFERENT FACTS AT YOUR DISPOSAL
THAN HE TALKS ABOUT?
I MEAN, DID YOU FEEL IT WAS
DELIBERATE, HE DIDN'T WANT TO
MAKE TIME FOR YOU BECAUSE OF
WHAT YOU SAID?
LET'S PLAY WHAT HE'S ACTUALLY
SAID ABOUT YOU.
>> AND THERE IS NO PLACE BETTER
TO TALK ABOUT BORDER SECURITY,
WHETHER THEY LIKE IT OR NOT,
BECAUSE I HAVE BEEN HEARING A
LOT OF THINGS, OH THE WALL WON'T
MAKE THAT MUCH OF A DIFFERENCE?
YOU KNOW WHERE IT MADE A
DIFFERENCE?
RIGHT HERE IN EL PASO.
I DON'T CARE WHETHER THE SMAR A
REPUBLICAN OR A DEMOCRAT,
THEY'RE NUMBER OF CRAP WHEN THEY
SAY IT HASN'T MADE A BIG
DIFFERENCE.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL HEARING THAT?
WHAT WOULD YOU ANSWER BE TO
THAT?
>> I LOVE TO HEAR THAT OVER AND
OVER.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS, I'VE NEVER
BEEN AGAINST A PHYSICAL BARRIER
ON THE BORDER.
I THINK THAT'S PART AND PARCEL
TO AN ENTIRE PROCESS.
FROM A STRATEGY STAND POINT IS,
WE'RE IN CONTROL OF THE BORDERS,
WE'RE A SOVEREIGN NATION.
I'VE NEVER DISAGREED WITH THE
PRESIDENT ON THAT, ALL I'VE
TRIED TO DO IS CLARIFY HIS
COMMENTS THAT WE WERE NOT A
LAWLESS COMMUNITY WITH HIGH
CRIME RATES BEFORE THE FENCE
WENT UP UNDER THE BUSH
PRESIDENCY IN 2008.
CERTAINLY IT IS A CONTRIBUTING
FACTOR TOWARDS, TO OUR SAFETY
HERE, BUT IT IS -- IT WAS NOT
THE SOLE PANACEA PRIOR TO,
THAT'S ALL I'VE TRIED TO SAY.
I'VE NOT SPOKEN AGAINST PHYSICAL
BARRIERS OF ANY TYPE.
I THINK THAT'S A PART OF THAT
WHOLE PROCESS.
YOU MENTIONED EARLIER THERE IS
78 MILES OF FENCE IN THE EL PASO
SECTOR FOR THE BORDER CONTROL.
IT'S NOT CONTINUOUS.
A GROUP OF THE FENCING THAT WENT
UP UNDER THE BUSH ADMINISTRATION
IN 2008 WAS PRIMARILY A
REPLACEMENT OF ABOUT TEN MILES
OF CHAIN LINK THAT HAD HOLES IN
IT AND WITH FORESTS.
SO REALLY TO MY KNOWLEDGE, IT
WASN'T EXPANDING THE FENCING.
IT WAS MERELY IMPROVING IT.
>> AND TO YOUR POINT, I DO WANT
TO DIG DOWN, IT IS WORTH
CONSTANTLY PUTTING THE FACTS OUT
THERE ON THE CRIME FIGURES ON
WHAT THE BALL U WALL DID OR
DIDN'T DO AND HOW YOU RESPOND TO
THEM.
IT WAS INTERESTING, BETO
O'ROURKE TALKS ABOUT IT BEING
ONE OF THE SAFEST SECTORS.
IN CALIFORNIA, ALONG THE BORDER,
SORT OF MAKING A POINT THAT
ACTUALLY MANY OF THE CITIES
ALONG THE BORDER ARE SAFER THAN
THOSE FURTHER INLAND.
WOULD YOU AGREE WITH THAT?
>> WELL, FROM OUR STANDPOINT,
YES, FROM WHAT I UNDERSTAND,
EL PASO IS RANKED THE SAFEST
CITY.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO UNIFORM
CRIME STATISTICS REPORTED FROM
THE FBI OR TO THE FBI.
SO A LOT OF THAT HAS TO DO WITH
OUR POLICE FORCE AND OUR
COMMUNITY POLICING AND THE
THINGS THAT WE HAVE BEEN DOING
FOR MANY YEARS.
BUT THE ISSUE IS RELATED TO
VIOLENCE WHEN IT CAME TO OUR
REGION HAD TO DO WITH WHAT IS
WITH THE DRUG CARTELS WHEN THEY
WERE FIGHTING IT OUT A FEW YEARS
AGO.
IT NEVER CAME OVER TO EL PASS SO
WE HAVE A SIGNIFICANT LAW
ENFORCEMENT PRESENCE HERE.
PLUS WE HAVE A LARGE MILITARY
PRESENCE.
>> I WANT TO PUT UP THE GRAPH
RIGHT NOW TO TELL PEOPLE WHAT
YOU HAVE BEEN SAYING IN TERMS OF
THE SPIKE IN CRIME AND THE
TROUGH IN CRIME.
SO WE SEE IT WAS VERY HIGH CRIME
RATES IN THE EARLY '90s.
THEN IT STARTED TO DRAMATICALLY
OR DID DRAMATICALLY DROP OFF IN
2006 AND IT STAYED PRETTY LOW
AND THE WALL WAS BUILT AROUND
2008 AND IT WENT UP A BIT.
THE CRIME.
IT PRETTY MUCH STAYED PRETTY
LOW.
SO BASICALLY WHAT YOU ARE SAYING
AND THE GRASS SHOW AND THE FACTS
AND THE NU
EL PASO WAS GETTING SAFER AND
SAFER AND LESS AND LESS CRIME T
PREFER TO USE THE NOMENCLATURE
FENCE, IN CERTAIN NEIGHBORHOODS
FROM AN ANECDOTAL STANDPOINT,
THE RESIDENTS FEEL SAFE BECAUSE
OF THAT.
IT DID THE MOST DRAMATIC DROP IN
OUR CRIME RATE HAD TO OCCUR WITH
AUTOMOBILE THEFTS DURING THAT
TIME FRAME.
SO YOU DON'T HAVE THAT AS A
NUMBER BROKEN OUT.
BUT I'VE SEEN THAT.
BECAUSE WE HAD THE POOREST HOLES
IN THE CHAIN LINK FENCE WERE
COMING OVER, STEALING VEHICLES,
DRIVING THEM BACK TO JUAREZ AND
THAT FENCE HAD A SIGNIFICANT
IMPACT ON THAT SO I'VE SAID FROM
DAY ONE IT HAD AN IMPACT ON
CRIME.
IT HAD AN IMPACT ON THE FEELINGS
OF SECURITY IN CERTAIN
NEIGHBORHOODS.
BUT OVERALL THE CRIME RATE WOULD
NOT DRAMATICALLY DROP.
I FEEL LIKE MY JOB AS A MAYOR IS
TO EXPLAIN TO PEOPLE OUTSIDE
THAT WE WERE NOT LAWLESS CRIME
RIDDEN CITY BEFORE THE FENCE
CAME IN.
EL PASO IS A VIABLE COMMUNITY.
IT'S THE SIXTH LARGEST CITY IN
THE STATE OF TEXAS AND THE 19th
LARGEST CITY IN THE UNITED
STATES.
WE'RE A MAJOR PLAYER AND THE
REST OF THE WORLD NEEDS TO
UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> SO YOU JUST SAID, I DON'T
KNOW WHETHER YOU TERM IT A PETTY
CRIME OR NON-DRUG-RELATED CRIME
AND NON-VIOLENT CRIME.
YOU TALK ABOUT HOW IT STOPS SOME
AUTO THEFT AND PERHAPS PROPERTY
CRIMES AS WELL, SO THERE WAS
THAT POSITIVE AS PICTURE TO THE
FENCE.
BUT ON THE ISSUES THAT THE
PRESIDENT TALKS ABOUT, WHETHER
IT'S ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION WHETHER
IT'S DRUGS, YOU KNOW, HE'S
CONJURED UP YOU KNOW HOARDS OF
RACISTS AND MURDERS COMING OVER,
IT HAVEN HAD AN EFFECT, RIGHT
THE WALL?
IS THERE THAT CRISIS I GUESS I'M
TRYING TO SAY AT EL PASO AT THE
BORDER.
>>.
>> WELL, LET ME STATE THE
PHYSICAL BARRIERS, ACCORDING TO
CUSTOMS AND BORDER PROTECTION
AND THE POLICE DO CHANNEL PEOPLE
AND DRUG IN CERTAIN AREAS.
MOST OF THE DRUGS THAT ARE
PICKED UP ILLEGALLY COME THROUGH
OUR PORTS OF ENTRY.
SO A PHYSICAL BARRIER CHANNEL
PEOPLE IN A CERTAIN WAY.
BUT THEY'RE NOT THE TOTAL
RESOLUTION TO BORDER SECURITY.
WHICH NOBODY SEEMS TO FULLY
DEFINE ANYWAY OUT OF WALK.
BUT IF YOU LOOK AT THE GEOGRAPHY
OF TEXAS FROM EL PASO TO
BROWNSVILLE, IT'S ALMOST A
PHYSICAL IMPOSSIBILITY TO PUT A
FENCE FROM EL PASO TO
BROWNSVILLE.
YOU CAN PUT IT IN CERTAIN SPOTS.
BUT THE MAJORITY OF TEXAS IS
PRIVATE LAND.
>> THAT WON'T WORK.
YOU NEED MORE MAN POWER,
TECHNOLOGY, A COMBINATION OF ALL
OF THE ABOVE.
I WOULD RELY ON THE EXPERT THAT
BORDERLAND AND HOMELAND SECURITY
TO TELL US WHAT THEY REALLY
NEED.
>> DO YOU?
YOU SORT OF INTIMATED THAT
PERHAPS THOSE IN WASHINGTON ARE
NOT QUITE CLEAR ABOUT THE
PARAMETERS OF WHAT THEY SEEM TO
BE TALKING ABOUT.
WERE YOU SURPRISED WHEN THE
PRESIDENT, WE UNDERSTAND, DID
OFF SCRIPT AND AD LIBBED ABOUT
LOVING AND WANTING MORE LEGAL
IMMIGRATION INTO THE UNITED
STATES?
WHEN HE SAID THAT AND WHEN YOU
WERE LISTENING TO THE SPEECH,
WHAT DID YOU THINK?
>> WELL, I DO THINK THAT THAT IS
SOMETHING THAT NEEDS TO BE DONE.
I THINK THAT LOTTERY SYSTEM IS
NOT FUNCTIONING AT ALL.
MY FORMER FIRM WAS TRYING TO
BRING IN AN UNDERWRITER FROM
LOIDS OF LONDON FOR SEVERAL
YEARS AND THE LOTTERY SYSTEM
THEY LOCKED OUT EVERY YEAR FOR
THREE YEARS AND GAVE UP.
BUT WHEN WE'RE BELOW 4%
UNEMPLOYMENT, WE'VE GOT TO DO
SOMETHING MORE ON LEGAL
IMMIGRATION AND I'VE ALSO SAID
IF YOU ARE A DACA OR A DREAMER
AND YOU SERVE IN THE MILITARY,
IT OUGHT TO BE AUTOMATIC YOU GET
U.S. CITIZENSHIP IF YOU SO
DESIRE AND FOR THE OTHERS AS
WELL.
IF YOU ARE ALREADY HERE AND THAT
10 TO 12 MILLION GROUP THAT'S
HERE UNDER FALSE SOCIAL SECURITY
NUMBERS, BUT EARNING A LIVING
AND RAISING THEIR FAMILY AND NOT
INVOLVED IN ANY CRIMINAL
ACTIVITIES.
YOU BET THOSE PEOPLE AND YOU
GIVE THEM GREEN CARDS, SO THAT
THEY CAN HAVE LEGAL WAYS OF
PAYING TAXES AND FOUGHT JUST
BOGUS SOCIAL SECURED NUMBERS AND
ANYBODY THAT DOESN'T PASS A
CRIMINAL BACKGROUND CHECK OUGHT
TO BE DEPORTED.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY WE WILL DEAL
WITH THAT I KNOW WE HAVE FOLKS
THAT SAY, OH, THEY'RE HERE
ILLEGALLY, WE CAN'T DEAL WITH
IT.
MY COMMENT IS THE EGG IS ALREADY
BROKEN, DEAL WITH IT.
>> WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID AD
LIBBED DURING THE STATE OF THE
UNION, DO YOU FEEL THAT WAS A
PART OF BE RIGHT BACKING BREAKI
THE EGG, IN OTHER WORDS MOVING
ALONG THE ROAD OF ACCEPTING WHAT
YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT, THAT
THERE NEEDS TO BE MORE LEGAL
IMMIGRATION AND PROPER
IMMIGRATION REFORM?
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS A UNIQUE
PERSONALITY WITHIN THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY.
HE'S THE PRESIDENT THAT WE'VE
NEVER SEEN BEFORE LIKE HIM HIM
I'M NOT SURE WE'LL SEE AFTER
HIM.
BUT HE IS IN A POSITION TO BE
ABLE TO DO SOME THINGS THAT I
THINK OTHERS MAY NOT HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO TO.
SO I WOULD HOPE HE WOULD MOVE
FORWARD WITH THAT.
HE'S INTIMATED ABOUT IMMIGRATION
REFORM AND OUR NATION NEEDS IT.
>> WELL, YOU ARE A POLITICIAN,
MAYOR.
AND YOU'VE ACCURATELY DESCRIBED
THE PRESIDENT.
HE'S A UNIQUE OPERATION IN THE
POLITICAL AFFIRMAMENT, BUT ONE
THAT MIGHT BE ABLE TO GET
CERTAIN THINGS DONE.
DO YOU SEE THAT HAPPENING AND
THE POSSIBILITY OF THAT
HAPPENING BY HIS HACKSS, BY HIS
POLIT
POLITICKING, ON IMMIGRATION, FOR
INSTANCE?
AS WE HAVE JUST BEEN DISCUSSING?
IN OTHER WORDS, DO YOU THINK HE
CAN DELIVER AS YOU HAVE
DESCRIBED?
>> I THINK IF HE WANTS TO, HE
CAN DELIVER.
YES.
SO IT'S UP TO HIM TO DETERMINE
THAT.
I WOULD BE HOPEFUL THAT HE
WOULD.
>> RIGHT.
SO LET'S ASK YOU AGAIN TO TALK
ABOUT THE REAL TRAGEDY THAT WE
SEE, WHICH IS A HUMAN TRAGEDY OF
ALL THIS CONFLATION OF ILLEGAL
AND ASYLUM AND THESE CHILDREN
AND FAMILIES BEING SEPARATED AT
THE BORDER AND THIS HORRENDOUS
SITUATION DOES NOT SEEM TO BE
GETTING ANY BETTER.
IN FACT, ESSENTIALLY THE WORSE
EWOULD LIKE TO PLEAS PLAY FOR
YOU THE DETENTION WHEN WE SPOKE
ACTUALLY BACK IN JUNE.
>> WE HAVE BEEN GIVEN NO
INFORMATION REGARDING THE
CHILDREN, WHERE THEY ARE.
ALL WE KNOW IS THEY ARE BEING
DISTRIBUTED THROUGHOUT THE
UNITED STATES, WHICH WAS A
SURPRISE TO COME OF US.
WE HEARD ABOUT THEM BEING PLACED
IN MICHIGAN, NEW YORK, RHODE
ISLAND, ELSEWHERE, THAT'S THE
REASON WE CAME TOGETHER AS A
GROUP OF MAYORS TO SAY ENOUGH IS
ENOUGH.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
THIS IS NOT WHAT WE ARE ABOUT AS
A NATION.
>> SO, MAYOR, THAT WAS IN JUNE,
HAVE THINGS GOTTEN BETTER NEAR
WHERE YOU ARE?
BECAUSE THERE ARE REPORTS THAT
ARE VERY, VERY UPSETTING TO
READ.
I WANT TO KNOW IN YOUR LOCATION,
HAVE THINGS GOTTEN BETTER?
>> THE NUMBERS ARE INCREASING.
WE'RE GETTING SOMEWHERE BETWEEN
3 AND 400 A DAY.
THESE ARE FAMILIES.
THEY'RE NOT BEING SEPARATED.
THE TORNEO SHELTER THAT WAS AT
THE TIME UP FOR UNACCOMPANIED
MINORS THAT I VISITED LAST
SUMMER WAS DISBANDED IF JANUARY.
AND THEY WENT OFF TO THEIR
SPONSORS.
AS I SAID, WE GET, THE WORD I
HAVE PER DAY IS ABOUT 3 TO 400.
THEY'RE PROCESSED THROUGH --
THEY COME INTO EMPASS SO ONCE
DISCHARGED FROM I.C.E. AND OUR
NGO, THE ENUNCIATION HOUSE HAS
APPROXIMATELY 20 SHELTERS IT
COORDINATES AND THEY ARE HERE,
FAMILIES TOGETHER.
THE PARENTS ARE GIVEN ANKLE
BRACELETS IN THE PROCESS AND
THEN THEY GO OFF TO THEIR
SPONSORS.
THEY HAVE BUS FARE, AIR FAIR,
WHATEVER IT IS THAT DOES THAT,
WHATEVER THEY NEED.
THEY'RE HERE USUALLY 24 TO A
MAXIMUM OF 48 HOURS, SOME AS
LONG AS 96 HOURS.
BUT I DON'T KNOW THAT YOUR
VIEWERS FULLY UNDERSTOOD WHEN
CPP, CPP IS A LAW ENFORCEMENT
AGENCY AND THE WAY IT WAS
STRUCTURED IS THAT HHS WOULD BE
THE ENTITY THAT WOULD BE
EQUIPPED TO TAKE CARE OF THOSE
THAT WERE HELD IN DETENTION AND
THEY'VE FIT DOING THAT.
I THINK THERE WAS A 9th CIRCUIT
COURT DECISION, AS I'M TOLD,
THAT SAYS CAN'T HOLD ANY
IMMIGRANTS THAT ARE SEEKING
ASYLUM LONGER THAN 20 DAYS.
SO THEY'RE PROCESSING THEM,
RELEASING THEM TO THEIR
SPONSORS.
>> SO YOU MENTIONED THE BOARD OF
PROTECTION UNIT AND I CONTRACTOR
AND THE LPG SERVICES.
WHAT DOES IT FEEL LIKE AS I LET
YOU GO'S MAYOR OF EL PASO THAT
YOUR CITY IS BEING REALLY A
PUNCHING BACK AND SORT OF IN THE
MIDDLE OF ALL OF THIS VERY, VERY
YOU KNOW HEATED POLITICS AND TO
AN EXTENT FAKE NEWS FOR A LONG
TIME.
>> WELL, I'M DOING MY BEST TO
TRY TO ARTICULATE THE CORRECT
STORY OF WHERE WE ARE AS WELL AS
EXPLAINING THAT WE ARE IN FAVOR
OF A SAFE BORDER AND THAT IS A
SOVEREIGN NATION AND YOU NEED TO
CONTROL OUR BORDERS, BUT THAT
EL PASO IS A VIABLE COMMUNITY, A
CONTRIBUTING COMMUNITY AND HAS A
CLOSE RELATIONSHIP BICULTURALLY
AND BINATIONALLY.
FAMILIES ON BOTH SIDE AND
COMMERCE WITH MEXICO.
I MEAN WE HAVE SIX BRIDGES THAT
HAVE 23,000 ILLEGAL PEDESTRIANS
COMING NORTH EVERY DAY.
I GOT 21 MILLION PRIVATE
PASSENGER VEHICLES THAT COME
NORTH ON AN ANNUAL BASIS.
WE GOT $82 BILLION OF TRADE
IMPORTS AND EXPORTS THAT GO
THROUGH HERE.
I MEAN WE'RE A MAJOR PLAYER AND
VERY MUCH INTERTWINED WITH
MEXICO, IF YOU WANT TO KNOW THE
BORDER, COME TO EMPASS SO.
>> ALL RIGHT MAYOR OF EMPASS SO,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR BEING
HERE WITH US.
>>> SO, WITH ALL THIS
POLITICKING, THERE ARE REAL
FLESH AND BLOOD PEOPLE WHO ARE
AFFECTED ON A DAILY BASIS.
THE MOST CONTROVERSIAL TRUMP
IMMIGRATION POLICY HAS NOT BEEN
THE WALL, BUT AS I MENTIONED
CHILD SEPARATION, DELIBERATELY
REMOVING MIGRANT CHILDREN FROM
THEIR PARENTS WHO ARE THEN
DETAINED.
A NEW INSPECTOR GENERAL REPORT
REVEALS THOUSANDS MORE WERE
SEPARATED FROM THEIR FAMILY
PREVIOUSLY ACKNOWLEDGED.
THE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND
HUMAN SERVICE FRS HAD TOO HOUSE
THE CHILDREN AND TESTIFYING ON
CAPITOL HILL RECENTLY COMMANDER
JONATHAN WHITE SAYS HE BELIEVES
THE POLICY HAD CATASTROPHIC
IMPLICATIONS.
>> SO THIS PROBLEM IS NOT OVER
EVEN AFTER THEY UNIFY THE CHILD
WITH THEIR FAMILY.
RIGHT?
>> THE CONSEQUENCES OF
SEPARATION FOR MANY CHILDREN
WILL BE LIFE LONG.
>> LET'S BE CLEAR IS THERE A
NULLIFICATION OF RETRAUMATIZE OR
IS THIS AN ADDITIONAL TRAUM THAT
ADDS ADDITIONAL STRESS AND
ADDITIONAL HARM TO A CHILD AFTER
THEY EXPERIENCE THE DIFFICULTIES
THAT THEY EXPERIENCED IN THEIR
HOME COUNTRY GOING THROUGH THE
LONG TREK?
DID HE ADD ADDITIONAL
RETRAUMIZATION TO THAT CHILD?
>> MANY CHILDREN THAT IS A ABLE
CONSEQUENCE, YES.
>> SO WE'RE GOING TO DIG DOWN
NOW INTO THE HUMANITY OF THAT
FACT AND THE LAW.
ED LAREN DARRAGH REPORTED
EXTENSIVELY ON THE BORDER AND
CHILD SEPARATION.
HE'S JOINING US FROM EL PASO.
MARY BOWER IS A DEPUTY DIRECTOR
FOR THE POVERTY LAW CENTER WHICH
REPRESENTS IMMIGRANTS IN
DETENTION.
SHE TRAVELED ALSO TO THE BORDER.
AND SHE IS JOINING US FROM
CHARLOTTESVILLE, VIRGINIA.
WELCOME TO YOU BOTH.
I JUST WANT TO ASK YOU, ED,
START OFF WITH SOME STORIES
ACTUALLY FROM BOTH OF YOU.
ED, YOU ARE THERE IN EL PASS SO
YOU JUST HEARD THE MAYOR.
TELL ME WHAT YOU HAVE SEEN AND
WHAT HAVE YOU REPORTED ON THE
HUMAN STORIES THAT IS BEHIND ALL
THESE POLITICS?
>>.
>> I THINK THE IMPORTANT THING
IS HOW FLUID THINGS CLANG ON THE
BORDER.
THE REASON WHY SOME PEOPLE MIGHT
TRY TO MIGRATE INTO THE UNITED
STATES IN 2018 AND 9019 IS BIFF
THAN THREE OR FOUR YEARS AGO.
>> THAT HAS BEEN THE CHALLENGE
WE HAVE SEEN HERE ALONG THE
U.S.-SOUTHERN BORDER OVER THE
COURSE OF THE LAST MONTH, WHERE
REALLY WE HAVE SEEN THE ARRIVAL
OF FAMILY UNITS, FAMILIES
ARRIVING WITH CHILDREN.
THAT IS A RELATIVELY NEW
PHENOMENON THAT YOU ARE SEEING
HERE ON THE U.S. SOUTHERN
BORDER.
BECAUSE OF THAT, THERE HAVE BEEN
SOME LAW MAKERS WHO HAVE
CRITICIZED THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION FOR NOT ADAPTING
QUICK ENOUGH TO DEALING WITH THE
SPECIFIC TYPE OF PEOPLE WHO ARE
ARRIVING HERE AT THE U.S.
SOUTHERN BORDER.
SO THAT'S WHY IT'S LED TO THIS
DRAMATIC INCREASE IN CHILDREN
SEPARATED FROM THEIR PARENTS.
IT WAS A PLAN THE ADMINISTRATION
HOPED A ZERO POLICY WOULD SERVE
AS A DETERRENT TO MIKE GRANTS
COMING MOSTLY FROM CENTRAL
AMERICAN COMPANIES TO DETER THEM
E THEM FROM COMING TO THE UNITED
STATES.
EVEN THOUGH THE ADMINISTRATION
SAYS THAT POLICY HAS BEEN
STOPPED, WE HEARD THE STORY OVER
HERE OVER THE COURSE OF A
MONTH-AND-A-HALF A YOUNG GIRL
SEPARATED FROM HER FATHER AT THE
END OF DECEMBER.
IT TOOK ALMOST A MONTH FOR THAT
GIRL TO BE REUNITED WITH HER
FAMILY.
THESE STORIES HAVE RAISED
QUESTIONS TO WHAT EXTENT THESE
CHILD SEPARATION CASES ARE STILL
UNFOLDING.
>> LET ME TURN TO YOU, MARY
BOWER, YOU DEAL WITH THIS FROM
YOUR LEGAL PERSPECTIVE.
THERE IS ALSO A HUMANITARIAN
PERSPECTIVE.
DESCRIBE THE EXTENT OF WHAT ARE
YOU SEEING IN.
THE SECRETARY GENERAL SAYS
THOUSANDS MORE HAVE BEEN
SEPARATED THAN EVER HAS BEEN
ACKNOWLEDGED.
IN OTHER WORDS THE PROBLEM IS
WORSE THAN WE THOUGHT IT WAS.
>> IT ABSOLUTELY IS WORSE.
WHAT WE SEE IS FAMILY SEPARATION
HAS EVOLVED.
IT'S TAKEN A SLIGHTLY DIFFERENT
FORM.
THERE ARE 10,000 KIDS DETAINED
NOW ACROSS THE UNITED STATES
BECAUSE OF A DELIBERATE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION POLICY AND IT'S
NOT AS THERE ARE THE PREVIOUS
SPEAKER INDICATED, A FAILURE TO
ADAPT.
IT IS A DELIBERATE AND NEFARIOUS
POLICY WHERE THE ADMINISTRATION
DECIDED THAT THEY WERE GOING TO
TAKE ACTIONS THAT WOULD RESULT
IN KIDS BEING DETAINED LONGER
AND IN PARENTS AND SPONSORS
BEING TURNED OVER TO
DEPORTATION.
THAT'S WHAT WE ARE SEEING.
WE ARE SEEING MORE THAN 10,000
KIDS LOCKED UP.
MOST WHO DON'T NEED TO BE LOCKED
UP.
>> JUST TO FOLLOW UP ON THAT,
NOW THAT WE KNOW MORE AND THIS
HAS BEEN THE CASE OF GREAT
CONTENTION AND ANGER IN THE
UNITED STATES AND ACTUALLY
AROUND THE WORLD.
ARE YOU ABLE TO DEEM WITH THESE?
ARE YOU ABLE TO HIGHLIGHT THESE
CASES?
IS THE LAW RESPONDING FAST
ENOUGH?
I MEAN, CAN YOU GET THEM
REUNITED WITH THEIR FAMILIES?
WHAT IS THE SITUATION ON THAT
LEVEL, MARY?
>> WELL, WE HAVE BROUGHT A CLASS
ACTION LAWSUIT ON BEHALF OF ALL
KIDS WHO ARE DETAINED ACROSS THE
UNITED STATES.
BUT WE KNOW THAT ANY CHILD WHO
IS LOCKED UP AND SEPARATED FROM
FAMILY IS EXPERIENCING A TRAUM.
WE KNOW THAT.
WE KNOW THESE KIDS WILL
EXPERIENCE LONG-TERM TRAUMA,
BECAUSE THEY ARE SEPARATED FROM
THEIR PARENTS SO WE'RE WORKING
TO REUNITE THEM AS QUICKLY AS
POSSIBLE.
BUT THIS DOES NOT HAVE TO BE.
THIS IS THE RESULT OF
CALCULATED, DELIBERATE
INTENTIONAL ACTS TO SEPARATE
KIDS FROM THEIR PARENTS AND TO
USE THE CHILDREN ESSENTIALLY AS
BAIT TO LURE THEIR PARENTS INTO
THE DEPORTATION SYSTEM AND
THAT'S WHAT WE ARE SEEING PLAY
OUT.
>> I'M GOING TO GET BACK TO THE
LEGAL REMEDY TO THIS I WANT TO
FOLLOW UP WITH ED ON YOU KNOW
YOU ARE SEEING EVERY DAY THESE
STORIES.
ED YOU HAVE BEEN SEEING THEM,
TOO, ON A REGULAR BASIS.
YOU HAVE BEEN REPORTING ON THEM.
GIVE ME A SENSE OF WHAT YOU SEE
THE KIDS THE FAMILIES, HOW
THEY'RE BEING AFFECTED THE
TRAUMAS.
>> Reporter: YEAH, I THINK A LOT
OF PEOPLE WHO ARRIVE AND I SPENT
A LOT OF TIME IN SHELTERS ON THE
MEXICAN SIDE OF THE BORDER,
THESE FAMILIES WHO HAVE MADE THE
LONG JOURNEY FROM THEIR CENTRAL
AMERICAN COUNTRY HOMES AND TO
GET THERE.
AND MANY TIMES WHEN I SPEAK TO
THEM, THEY KIND OF SEEM
OBLIVIOUS, NOT AWARE AS TO THE
EXTENT OF HOW MUCH THIS IS BEING
DEBATED HERE IN THE UNITED
STATES.
THE AMOUNT OF MISTAKES
INFORMATION THAT THEY'RE GIVEN E
GIVING IN THEIR HOME COUNTRIES
AND ESSENTIALLY LURED BY
CRIMINAL AND ORGANIZED GANGS
THAT BRING THEM THROUGH CENTRAL
AMERICA INTO MEXICO AND TRY TO
GET THEM INTO THE UNITED STATES.
THIS IS HUGE BUSINESS FOR A LOT
OF THESE SMUGGLERS THAT GET THEM
HERE TO THE DOORSTEP OF THE
UNITED STATES AND ESSENTIALLY
WASH THEIR HANDS OF THEM.
THEN IT BECOMES, YOU KNOW ARC
DANGEROUS SITUATION FOR THEM.
SO YOU SEE A LOST CONFUSION AND
BY AND LARGE, I HAVE SPOKEN TO
HUNDREDS, DOZENS OF THESE PEOPLE
OVER THE COURSE OF MY REPORTING
HERE AND ON THE U.S.-SOUTHERN
BORDER FOR YEARS AND ALL OF THEM
REPEATEDLY TELL YOU THAT THEY
COME HERE SIMPLY LOOKING FOR ATE
BER OPPORTUNITY AND IN A CASE
RECENTLY OF THE CENTRAL AMERICAN
MIGRANT, MANY OF THEM TRYING TO
ESCAPE VIOLENCE.
THEY HAVE BEEN DIRECTLY
THREATENED BY GANGS IN THEIR
HOMETOWN.
THEY FEEL LIKE THE ONLY COURSE
OF ACTION THEY HAVE IS TO DROP
EVERYTHING AND RUN NORTH.
>> MARY, FROM A LEGAL POINT OF
VIEW AND THE PERSPECTIVE ON THE
BIG PICTURE, THE PRESIDENT IS
OFTEN GOING TO THE BOARD IR,
GOING TO EL PASO THIS EVENING
AND TALKING ABOUT THE RACISTS
AND THE -- RAPISTS AND CRIMINALS
AND GANGS AND MS-13, ET CETERA.
SORT OF INVOKING YOUNG MEN,
MIDDLE AGED MEN ADOLESCENTS.
FIRST AND FOREMOST, WHO ARE THE
MAJORITY OF PEOPLE COMING OVER?
ARE THEY THAT DEMOGRAPHIC?
AND WHERE ARE MOST OF THE
ILLEGALS?
ARE THEY COMING THROUGH BORDER
THE SOUTHERN BORDER?
WHERE IS THE CENTER OF GRAVITY
ON THIS ISSUE?
>> THEY'RE NOT THE PEOPLE DONALD
TRUMP DESCRIBED, THEY'RE NOT
RAPISTS AND MURDERERS.
THE PEOPLE COMING TO UNITED
STATES WE ARE SEEING DEBORDEER
ARE DESPERATE PEOPLE TERRIFIED
AND FLEEING VIOLENCE.
THEY'RE COMING TO THE UNITED
STATES.
IN MANY CASES THEY WOULD LIKE TO
APPLY FOR ASYLUM AT THE PORT OF
ENTRY AND THEY CANNOT BECAUSE OF
ADMINISTRATION POLICIES.
WE SEE THAT IN TERMS OF THE
NUMBERS OF UNDOCUMENTED PEOPLE.
THE MAJORITY OF THE UNDOCUMENTED
PEOPLE IN THE UNITED STATES NOW
ARE ACTUALLY COMING IN THROUGH
AIRPORTS, PEOPLE OVERSTAYING
VISAS.
SO ALL OF THE RED RICK FROM
TRUMP ABOUT WHO IMMIGRANTS ARE
AND WHY THEY'RE COMING AND WHAT
THEY'RE SEEKING, IT'S JUST
WRONG.
IT'S JUST DEMONSTRABLY WRONG.
WE KNOW THAT WE KNOW IMMIGRANTS
ARE FAR LESS LIKELY TO COMMIT
CRIMES THAN U.S. CITIZENS.
WE KNOW ALL OF THAT.
>> WE HEARD BETO O'ROURKE SAY
THAT THE MAYOR OF EL PASO,
TEXAS, TALKING ABOUT HIS
PRACTICALLY CRIME-FREE LOCATION
THERE IN EL PASO.
CAN YOU JUST SEPARATE FOR US
WHAT APPEARS TO BE A CONSISTENT
CONFLATION OF THE ISSUES?
THERE'S LEGAL.
THEN THERE'S ILLEGAL.
THERE'S ASYLUM SEEKERS.
MARY, JUST TELL US, WHO EACH
GROUP IS AND HOW EACH NEEDS TO
BE DEALT WITH.
>> WELL, I THINK WE HAVE TO ACT
KNOWLEDGE FIRST THAT CONSTANT
RHETORIC ABOUT HOW HE WANTS
PEOPLE TO DO THINGS LEGALLY IS
ALSO DEMONSTRABLY WRONG.
RIGHT?
BECAUSE HE'S NOT ALLOWING PEOPLE
TO APPLY AT THE PORTS OF ENTRY.
HE IS PUTTING UP HUGE OBSTACLES
TO ALLOW PEOPLE TO APPLY FOR
ASYLUM TO BE ABLE TO DO THAT.
HE HAS TAKEN BASICALLY A MILLION
PEOPLE WHOARE HERE UNDOCUMENTED
AND TRIED TO MAKE THEM ILLEGAL
BY TRYING TO TERMINATE DACA AND
CPS.
HE HAS UNDERGONE POLICY AFTER
POLICY AFTER POLICY, THAT IS
DESIGNED TO ATTACK PEOPLE WHO
ARE HERE BOTH LAWFULLY AND
UNLAWFULLY AND TO ATTACK THE
SYSTEM OF IMMIGRATION AND ASYLUM
AT ITS ROOTS TO MAKE THAT
UNAVAILABLE TO PEOPLE.
SO WE KNOW THAT RHETORIC ABOUT
HOW PEOPLE NEED TO STAND IN LINE
OR HOW THEY NEED TO DO IT
LEGALLY.
>> THAT IS BELIED BY THE ACTIONS
OF ADMINISTRATION THIS
ADMINISTRATION.
THEY DON'T WANT PEOPLE TO DO
THAT THEY DON'T WANT IMMIGRATION
AT ALL.
THEY HAVE MADE THAT CLEAR
THROUGH THEIR POLICY.
YES, WE NEED TO HAVE AN
IMMIGRATION REFORM THAT LETS 11
MILLION OR SO HERE OUT OF
STATUS.
WE NEED TO HAVE THAT KIND OF
REFORM.
WE HAVE NEEDED THAT FOR WELL
OVER A DECADE OR TWO.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN THAT WE
PUT UP A WALL AND DENY THE
ABILITY TO APPLY ASYLUM TO
PEOPLE WHO ARE DESPERATE AND ON
OUR DOORSTEP.
WE ENACTED THE ASYLUM LAW IN THE
WAKE OF WORLD WAR II EXACTLY SO
THIS WOULD NOT HAPPEN AGAIN.
BECAUSE THE WEST WAS ASHAMED, IT
HAD TURNED AWAY JEWS DURING THE
HOLOCAUST.
WE SAID NEVER AGAIN WE DON'T
WANT TO TURN OUR BACK ON
DESPERATE PEOPLE AT OUR
DOORSTEP.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE ASYLUM LAWS
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
WE ARE SHAMEFULLY, SHAMEFULLY,
IGNORING OUR LEGAL MORAL
RESPONSIBILITY HERE.
>> LET ME ASK YOU TO STAND ON
THAT, YOU SEE IT, YOU REPORT ON
THE PEOPLE.
AND THERE IS THIS POLICY THAT
THE PRESIDENT INPLEMTED CALLED
METERING WHICH LIMITS THE NUMBER
OF ASYLUM SPEAKERS ALLOWED TO
ENTER THE UNITED STATES EACH DAY
AND THEY ARE HELD IN DETENTION
CENTERS OR CENTRES ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE BORDER.
MEANING THEY HAVE TO WAIT MONTH
TO MONTH FOR THEIR CLAIMS ARE
PROCESSED.
WHAT IS THAT DOING AT THE
BOARDER?
THE PRESIDENT CLAIMS A CRISIS AT
THE BORDER.
IS THIS A PART, ED, OF THE
CRISIS?
IS IT MANUFACTURING A CRISIS, IF
YOU LIKE?
>> Reporter: I THINK, MARY
BRINGS UP AN IMPORTANT POINT YOU
GUYS ARE HITTING ON.
THAT'S THE NEWEST ANGLE OF WHAT
WE ARE SEEING IN OUR REPORTING
ALONG THE U.S.-SOUTHERN BORDER.
RIGHT NOW MENTIONED THIS
METERING SYSTEM.
SO PEOPLE UNDERSTAND WHAT IT'S
LIKE.
IMAGINE A GROUP, VERY LARGE
GROUPS SHOWING UP IN VARIOUS
SECTION OF THE U.S. SOUTHERN
BORDER.
IT'S NOT UNCOMMON TO SEE 200,
300 MIKE GRANTS SHOW UP IN A
BORDER TOWN IN A REMOTE AREA AND
THEY COME TO JUAREZ, FOR
EXAMPLE, THEY'RE AT THE PORT OF
ENTRY, THEN THE U.S. MIGHT HAVE
A SYSTEM IN PLACE, I THINK IT
VARIES BETWEEN WHICH PORT OF
ENTRY YOU COME INTO.
TODAY THEY SAY WE WILL TAKE 15
ASYLUM SEEK ESSER, TODAY 12 THE
DAY BEFORE NINE.
THAT'S NOT LETTING EVERYBODY
COME IN.
THAT'S FORCING PEOPLE TO WHITE
ON THE MEXICAN SIDE OF THE
BORDER AND THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION IS ALSO FLIRTING
WITH THE IDEA, I THINK THERE IS
A PROGRAM INITIALLY PUT IN PLACE
IN TIJUANA ON THE BORDER OF
CALIFORNIA ESSENTIALLY FORCING
FAMILY UNITS TO WAIT OUT THEIR
ASYLUM CLAIMS ON THE MEMBERS KA
SIDE OF THE BORDER.
THERE IS SOME TALK OF EXPANDING
THAT PROGRAM ON VARIOUS POINTS
OF THE SOUTHERN BORDER.
THIS, THE CRITICS OF THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN WHAT
THEY SEE AS A DETRIMENTAL ISSUE
THAT WILL CONTINUE TO PUT THESE
FAMILIES AND THESE CHILDREN IN
HARM'S WAY.
YOU ARE ESSENTIALLY ASKING
PEOPLE COMING HERE AND ASKING
FOR A LEGAL PROCESS, REQUESTING
ASYLUM AND FORCING THEM TO WAIT
IN THESE COMMUNITIES ALONG THE
U.S.-SOUTHERN BORDER, WHERE THEY
ARE MUCH MORE, THERE IS MUCH
MORE DANGEROUS SITUATIONS BEING
TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF, THREATENED,
THAT SORT OF THING.
>> THAT IS THE CONCERN FOR A LOT
OF ORGANIZATIONS THAT ARE TRYING
TO HELP THESE MIGRANTS WHO ARE
ARRIVING HERE IN THESE BORDER
REGIONS.
>> CAN I JUST ASK YOU, MARY, ED,
IF EITHER OF YOU KNOW, THERE
HAVE BEEN REPORTS RECENTLY OF
TWO KIDS THAT DIED IN ONE OF
THESE CENTRES IN MEXICO.
IS IT FACTUALLY CORRECT HOW THAT
HAPPENED?
ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT THE
HAPPENING MORE?
>> IT IS FACTUALLY CORRECT.
WE KNOW THAT THREE CHILDREN WERE
KIDNAPPED IN TIJUANA.
THEY HAD BEEN STAYING AT A YOUTH
SHELTER BECAUSE THEY WERE NOT
ALLOWED TO APPLY FOR ASYLUM.
TWO WERE MERD D MURDERED.
ONE WAS ALLOWED TO ESCAPE AND
BRING BACK THE MESSAGE BASICALLY
THAT CHILDREN ARE IN DANGER AND
CHILDREN ARE IN DANGER.
FAMILIES ARE IN DANGER.
THERE IS A DANGEROUS WAY TO
CONDUCT A POLICY.
THIS MEANS THAT PEOPLE ARE
TRAPPED IN BORDER CITIES WHERE
USERS AND GOONGS AND THE FOLKS
THAT PEOPLE ARE FLEEING KNOW
PEOPLE ARE TRAPPED AND SO PEOPLE
ARE IN GRAVE DANGER.
PEOPLE HAVE DIED BECAUSE OF THE
POLICIES.
MORE PEOPLE WILL DIE UNLESS THIS
POLICY IS CHANGED.
WE KNOW THAT THAT IS ON OUR
HANDS.
>> ON THIS SIDE OF THE BORDER,
LET ME PLAY ANOTHER LITTLE CLIP
FROM COMMANDER, THE COMMANDER
WHO WE HEARD, JONATHAN WHITE
FROM HHS.
WE HEARD HIM IN THE LEAD-IN
TALKING ABOUT THE TRAWLER FOR
THE KIDS.
HE TALKED ABOUT THIS POLICY OF
HOUSING SEPARATED CHILDREN, HE
HAD TO ENFORCE IT.
HE NEVER WOULD HAVE ENFORCED
THIS POLICY HIMSELF.
JUST LISTEN TO THIS.
>> THE CONCERN WHICH I EXPRESSED
WERE TWO.
FIRST, THAT THIS WOULD BE
INCONSISTENT WITH OUR LEGAL
REQUIREMENT TO ACT IN THE BEST
INTEREST OF THE CHILD AND WOULD
EXPOSE CHILDREN TO UNNECESSARY
RISK OF HARM.
SECOND, THAT IT WOULD EXCEED THE
CAPACITY OF THE PROGRAM, ISSUES
OF THAT CAPACITY ARE VERY
IMPORTANT BECAUSE IT CONSTITUTES
OUR ABILITY TO PROVIDE A SAFE
AND APPROPRIATE ENVIRONMENT TO
EVERY CHILD.
>> WE'VE ONLY GOT FIRST TIME
SECONDS LEFT, ED LAVANDARA, IN
YOUR REPORTING, HAVE YOU HEARD
SIMILAR MISTAKES GIVINGS FROM
OFFICIALS WHO HAVE TO ENFORCE
SOME OF THIS POLICY?
>> Reporter: THAT TO ME THAT WAS
THE FIRST TIME I HAVE HEARD
PEOPLE IN AN OFFICIAL CAPACITY
SAY THAT THAT WAS MADE THAT
STATEMENT THERE IN THAT
CONGRESSIONAL SETTING SO
STRIKING.
>> WELL, MARY, DO YOU ALWAYS
FIND IT EXTRAORDINARY OR HAVE
YOU HEARD IT BEFORE?
>> NO, THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME I
HAVE HEARD THAT.
THAT IS THE CONGRESS AM
STATEMENT OF ATTEMPT THEY ARE
SUPPOSED TO BE ACTING IN THE
BEST ACTION OF CHILDREN.
WHAT WE SEE THAT HAS NOT BEEN
HANG, JUST THE OPPOSITE HAS BEEN
HAPPENING.
>> MARY BOWER, ED LAVANDARA,
THANK YOU FOR JOINING ME THIS
EVENING.
>>> NOW WE DIG INTO AMERICA'S
COMPLICATED RELATIONSHIP WITH
DATA AND UNDER SURVEILLANCE.
MICHAEL CHERTOFF WAS PRESIDENT
GEORGE W. BUSH'S HOMELAND
SECURITY SECRETARY.
BUT BEFORE THAT HE MADE A NAME
FOR HIMSELF CO-AUTHORING THE
U.S. PATRIOT ACT IN THE WAKE OF
THE 9/11 ATTACKS.
THE ACT MASSIVELY EXPANDED
GOVERNMENT UNDER SURVEILLANCE.
IT ALLOWED THE DETENTION OF
IMMIGRANTS, SOME THINK THE
SUPREME COURT STRUCK DOWN, NOW
CHERTOFF IS DISCUSSING THE
GROWING THREAT TO PRIVACY AS WE
HAT TOWN IS U DOWN WITH US AND
YES THEY TOUCHED ON THAT BORDER
WALL.
>>?
MICHAEL, LET'S START WITH THINGS
IN THE NEWS NOW AND ABSTRACT UP.
FIRST, IMMIGRATION.
YOU WERE THE SECOND HEAD OF
HOMELAND SECURITY AND SERVED
UNDER PRESIDENT BUSH.
HOW IMPORTANT IS A PHYSICAL
BARRIER THAT'S AT THE CENTER OF
ALL THIS?
>> IT'S A VERY SMALL PIECE OF
WHAT YOU WANT.
WHEN WE WERE IN OFFICE, I THINK
WE BUILT ABOUT 650 MILES OF
BARRIERS ALONG CERTAIN AREAS
WHERE YOU DISTANCE BETWEEN THE
BORDER AND SAY A MAJOR TONY OR A
HIGHWAY WAS VERY SHORT.
AND, THEREFORE, YOU WOULDN'T BE
ABLE TO INTERCEPT PEOPLE IF THEY
CROSSED THE BORDER.
YOU COULD PROBABLY BUILD ANOTHER
50 OR SO MILES AND FIND SOME
USEFUL PLACES FOR IT.
BUT IT'S ONLY A VERY SMALL PART
OF WHAT YOU WANT.
WHAT YOU REALLY NEED IS
TECHNOLOGY, BOARD PARE TROLL
PERSONNEL, A DETENTION
FACILITIES FOR PEOPLE WHO WILL
BE DEPORT AND IT HAS TO BE
INTEGRATED INTO A SYSTEM.
SO THE IDEA THAT YOU WANT A WALL
IS A MISTAKES CHARACTERIZATION
FOR WHAT THE REAL REQUIREMENT
IS.
>> IS IT WORTH SHUTTING THE
GOVERNMENT OVER?
>> IT'S NOT WORTH SHUTTING THE
GOVERNMENT OVER.
THE DISAPPOINTING THING IS IF
YOU ACTUALLY GOT THE
PROFESSIONALS TOEBLG, THEY COULD
MAP OUT PRETTY CLEARLY GIVEN
WHAT THEY KNOW EXACTLY WHERE YOU
WANT PHYSICAL BARRIERS, WHERE
YOU WANT TECHNOLOGY, WHERE YOU
WANT DRONES AND THAT WOULD BE
THE INTELLIGENT WAY TO SPEND THE
MONEY.
IRONICALLY, WHEN THERE IS
COMPLAINING ABOUT DRUGS COMING
THROUGH THE COUNTRY, THE VAST
MAJORITY OF THAT COMES THROUGH
THE PORTS OF ENTRY.
SO IF YOU HAD EQUIPMENT AT THE
PORTS OF ENTRY THAT WOULD ALLOW
YOU BETTER VISIBILITY TO WHAT IS
CONCEALED IN AN AUTOMOBILE AND
TRUCK, THAT WOULD DO MUCH MORE
TO REDUCE THE IMPLICATION OF
DRUGS AND BARRIERS IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE DESERT.
BARRIERS REALLY DISCOURAGE A
CERTAIN KIND OF CASUAL CROSSER.
IT DOESN'T DISCOURAGE SOMEONE
WHO IS INVESTING LARGE AMOUNTS
OF MONEY TO MOVE VERY VALUABLE
DRUGS AND THEY WANT VOLUME AND
THEY'RE GOING TO BASICALLY TRY
TO USE EXISTING TRANSPORTATION
SYSTEMS TO COME THROUGH PORTS OF
ENTRY.
>> EVEN IN A NATIONAL EMERGENCY?
>> I WOULDN'T SAY IT'S A
NATIONAL EMERGENCY.
OBVIOUSLY, BORDER PATROL IS AN
IMPORTANT FEDERAL OBJECTIVE.
ITEMLY THE RATE OF CROSSING
ALTHOUGH FLUCTUATING OVER TIME
HAS GENERALLY GONE DOWN.
WHAT'S REALLY DRIVING IT NOW IS
LARGELY CONDITIONS IN PARTS OF
CENTRAL AMERICA WHERE YOU HAVE,
NOT ONLY ECONOMIC ISSUES BUT
HAVE YOU GANG VIOLENCE, HAVE YOU
LACK OF RULE OF LAW AND PEOPLE
ARE FLEEING BECAUSE THEY'RE
AFRAID FOR THEIR LIVES THE BEST
WAY TO STOP THAT IS TO WORK WITH
THE CENTRAL AMERICAN GOVERNMENTS
TO REINSTITUTE THE RULE OF LAW
TO BUILD THE ECONOMY AND KEEP
THE WORLD HAPPY TO STAY IN THEIR
HOMES.
>> ANOTHER REASON, THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE LAID OUT
AN INDICTMENT AGAINST HAUWEI.
IF UNITED STATES HAS BEEN
PRESSURING OR LEVERAGE COUNTRIES
AROUND THE WORLD TO FOUGHT USE
EQUIPMENT FROM THIS TELECOM
COMPANY AS THE WORLD UPGRADES TO
35G.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT IT THAT'S
IMPORTANT?
>> THIS IS ACTUALLY NOT NEW.
THE ISSUE OF CHINESE TECHNOLOGY
HAS POTENTIALLY CREATING AN
OPPORTUNITY FOR THE CHINESE TO
EXIT ACTS OF ESPIONAGE OR ACTS
OF SABOTAGE HAS BEEN DISCUSSED
AMONG SECURITY PEOPLE FOR THE
LAST TEN YEARS OR SO WE SAW
EARLIER THIS YEAR AN INDICTMENT
OF HAUWEI FOR STEALING
TECHNOLOGICAL SECRETS FROM
T-MOBILE.
THAT'S HAPPENED IN THE PAST THAT
WILL CONTINUE TO HAPPEN.
BUT BEYOND THAT I THINK THERE IS
A CONCERN THAT YOU ARE
POTENTIALLY PUTTING THE NEXT
GENERATION OF CRITICAL
TECHNOLOGY IN THE HANDS OF A
COUNTRIES WHICH MAY BE AN
ADVERSARY IF CERTAIN RESPECTS.
WE'VE PUBLISHED A REPORT CALLED
FREEDOM ON THE NET AND IN THE
REPORT, WE DETAIL HOW THE
CHINESE ARE USING THE EXPLOITS
OF I.T. TECHNOLOGY TO EMBED
THEMSELVES AROUND THE WORLD IN
ASIA AND AFRICA AND THEY'RE
ACTUALLY TEACHING SOME OF THE
LOCAL GOVERNMENTS THERE HOW TO
USE TECHNOLOGY TO BETTER CONTROL
THE POPULOUS AND TO SUPPRESS
FREE SPEECH.
SO WE'RE IN A SITUATION NOW
WHERE IF YOU HAVE CHINESE
COMPANIES THAT ARE IN CRITICAL
NODES AROUND THE WORLD, ARE YOU
ESSENTIALLY, PROGRAMS, ENABLING
THE EXPORT AUTHORITARIANISM TO
PARTS OF THE WORLD THAT ARE
FREE.
>> HOW DO THE WEST COUNTER THAT?
IS FROM A WAY THAT YOU CAN GET
THE WORLD TO AGREE ON THE RULES
OF THE ROAD?
>> WELL, I DO THINK THERE ARE
THINGS THAT WE CAN DO, EASTERN
USING MULTI-STAKE HOLDER
APPROACH.
THEY'RE UNDER WAY RIGHT NOW.
FOR EXAMPLE, I THINK MANY OF THE
WESTERN COUNTRIES DO HAVE A MORE
OR LESS A COMMON SET OF VALUES
AND COULD REASONABLY REALLY
REACH AGREEMENTS ON SOME OF THE
THINGS WE ARE TALKING ABOUT AND
BECAUSE OF THE FACT THAT THESE
COUNTRIES ARE STILL
CORRECTIVELY, BY FAR, THE MOST
POWERFUL ECONOMIC ACTORS ON THE
GLOBE, IN THE END IF WE DO HAVE
A RESET OF VALUES AND AGREED
APPROACH, I THINK THAT CAN DRIVE
THE CHINESE TO ACCOMMODATE TO
THAT AS WELL.
AND I'M ON A GLOBAL COMMISSION
FOR STABILITY NOW WHICH HAS
DRAWN PEOPLE FOCUSING ON CYBER
ISSUES TO TRY TO COME UP WITH
SOME NORMS THAT CAN BE GLOBALLY
ACCEPTED TO HAVE AN OPEN
INTERNET, A FREE INTERNET AND AN
INTERNET THAT IS NOT FRAGMENTED
BUT RATHER IS TRULY GLOBAL IN
IT.
>> YOU WROTE A BOOK RECENTLY
TALKING ABOUT THE DATA EXPLOSION
AND HAVE YOU KIND OF A SIMPLE
IDEA IN DATA 1.0, 2.0, 3.0,
BREAK THAT DOWN FOR US?
>> I WROTE THE BOOK BECAUSE I
THOUGHT PEOPLE DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
THE MATTER IN WHICH DATA IS
BEING CHECKED AND HOW WE'RE
USING NEWS NOW AND HOW IT WILL
TRANSFORM THE WAY WE LIVE.
SO I LOOK BACK HISTORICALLY.
IF YOU LOOK AT MOST OF HUMAN
HISTORY, DATA WAS BASICALLY WHAT
YOU SAID WHAT YOU HEARD, WHAT
WAS WRITTEN DOWN, WHAT WAS
PUBLISHED AND WE WERE MAINLY
CONCERNED ABOUT PROTECTING OUR
PRIVACY IN THE SENSE OF OUR
PROPERTY.
IT WAS AN EXPRESSION HEARING.
EVERY MAN'S HOME IS HIS CASTLE.
IT GOES BACK A FEW HUNDRED YEARS
AND THE IDEA WAS YOUR PRIVACY IS
BACK TO YOUR PROPERTY.
NO ONE CAN ENTER THROUGH YOUR
HOUSE WITHOUT A WARRANT.
WHEN YOU GOT TO LESSEN, ALL OF A
SUDDEN PROPERTY WAS NOT THE
ISSUE ANYMORE.
IT WAS CONFIDENTIALITY.
COULD I KEEP MY CONVERSATIONS
PRIVATE?
COULD I KEEP MY IMAGE PRIVATE?
AND THEREFORE THE LAW STARTED TO
CHANGE, TO RECOGNIZE WE HAVE TO
FOCUS ON PROPERTY AND NOW WE
HAVE TO FOCUS CONFIDENTIALITY.
MY POINT NOW IS, GIVEN THE
AMOUNT OF DATA THAT IS BEING
GENERATED, NOT ONLY WHAT WE
VOLUNTARILY GENERATE BUT WHAT IS
GENERATED ABOUT US.
THE FACT THAT IT IS NOW STORED
INDEFINITELY.
IT CAN BE PUBLISHED ALL OVER THE
WORLD.
SHOULD WE TRY TO KEEP THINGS
HIDDEN OR SECRET?
THAT SHIP HAS SAILED.
NOW WE TALK ABOUT WHO CONTROLS
THE DATA?
WHAT IS YOUR RIGHT EVEN WHEN THE
DATA IS COLLECTED TO BE ABLE TO
SAY YES OR NO TO HOW IT'S BEING
USED?
>> THEY'RE ISSUING AUTONOMY.
>> EXACTLY.
IT'S ABOUT FREEDOM AND CHINA,
CHINA ARE WORKING ON A SOCIAL
CREDITOR, WHERE EVERYTHING THAT
YOU DO WILL BE COMPILED AND YOU
ESSENTIALLY GET A RATING AS TO
WHETHER YOU ARE A GOOD OR A BAD
THING.
IF YOU ARE GOOD, YOU GET
PREFERENCE AND ALL KIND OF
THINGS LIKE JOBS AND EDUCATION.
AND IF NOT, YOU COULD BE SHUT
OUT OF THINGS.
NOW IMAGINE THAT IN A WESTERN
SOCIETY, AND IT MIGHT BE
PRIVATE, WHERE YOUR ABILITY TO
GET A JOB OR GET INSURANCE OR
FIND A PLACE TO LIVE WOULD BE
AFFECTED BY WHETHER AN ALGORITHM
LOOKS AT EVERYTHING YOU DO,
THAT'S RECORDING IN SOME FORM OR
FAX OF DATA AND MAKES A JUDGMENT
OF WHETHER YOU ARE DESIRABLE OR
NOT A DESIRABLE PERSON.
>> ISN'T THAT STARTING TO HAPPEN
ALREADY?
IF A HEALTH INSURER HAD ACCESS
TO MY SHOPPING LIST, IT COULD
CHANGE MY RATES.
BEING REALLY HEALTHY AND MAYBE
EQUALS OUT PUT.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU HAVE A GYM
MEMBERSHIP LOCKING IN FIVE TIMES
A WEEK.
OKAY.
HE'S NOT GOING TO DIE, VERSUS A
BAG OF M AND AND Ms, NETFLIX
BINGEING.
>> BUT THAT'S HAPPENING NOW,
EVEN I PUBLISHED A BOOK ABOUT
SIX MONTHS AGO AND THERE ARE
MORE STORIES ABOUT INSURANCE
COMPANIES SAYING, WE WANT TO SEE
YOUR FitBit.
HOW MUCH EXERCISE ARE YOU
GETTING?
AND THEY'RE ALSO LOOKING AT
THINGS LIKE, EXACTLY WHAT FOODS
DO YOU EAT WHEN YOU GO TO A
RESTAURANT?
WHAT DO YOU EAT AT A RESTAURANT.
HOW WAS YOUR SLEEP PATTERN?
IMAGINE ALL OF THIS BEING
COLLECTED AND PRETTY SOON YOUR
FREEDOM TO DECIDE WHAT YOU WANT
TO DO WILL ALWAYS BE SUBJECT TO
A NAGGING FEAR THAT YOU ARE
GOING TO BE PUNISHED.
THERE WAS A BBC THAT WAS ON THAT
ACTUALLY TOOK THIS, I'D LIKE TO
SAY TO AN EXTREME, NOT THAT
EXTREME ABOUT A WORLD IN WHICH
LITERALLY EVERYBODY IS BEING
RAIDED UP AND DOWN MINUTE BY
MINUTE AND IT MAKES 1984,
GEORGERWELL'S DISTOPIAN NOVEL
LOOK LIKE A KINDER GAT INNER'S
DREAM THERE THIS IS THE GUY THAT
HELPED WRITE THE PATRIOT ACT.
AT THE TIME YOU WERE NOT IN THAT
DATA CLIMATE WE ARE IN TODAY.
THERE WASN'T AMAZON NEARLY AS
POWERFUL AND ALL KNOWING WHAT IT
IS.
WHAT IS THE BALANCE BETWEEN
GIVING THE GOVERNMENT THE
OPPORTUNITIES TO CHASE DOWN AND
GET AS MUCH INFORMATION, PREVENT
ATTACKS, ET CETERA?
AND THAT SENSE OF AUTONOMY THAT
YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT WHERE I
STILL FEEL LIKE I HAVE SOME
LEVEL OF CONTROL OVER WHAT I
CHOOSE TO SHARE WITH ESPECIALLY
THE BODY GOVERNING ME?
>> WELL, WE ARE RIGHT TO BE
CONCERNED ABOUT THE GOVERNMENT
AS WELL AS THE PRIVATE SECTOR.
WHAT IS INTERESTING IS THAT THE
GOVERNMENT OPERATES ON MUCH MORE
CONSTRAINTS THAN A PRIVATE
SECTOR.
THE GOVERNMENT DOESN'T EVEN
DREAM OF COLLECTING DIVINE
INFORMATION THAT'S COLLECTED IN
THE PRIME SECTOR AND BEFORE THE
GOVERNMENT USES IT, THERE ARE
ALL KIND OF DATES THEY HAVE TO
GO THROUGH, AT LEAST IN THE
UNITED STATES AND OTHER
COUNTRIES ARE ACTUALLY
DIFFERENT.
SO, FOR EXAMPLE, TO COLLECT
CONTENT OF INFORMATION E-MAILS
ARE BEING DISCUSSED OVER THE
TELEPHONE, EITHER ONE.
NOW THERE IS A MOVEMENT I THINK
FOR CORRECTLY TO REQUIRE A
WARRANT, EVEN FOR OLDER, NOT
JUST CURRENT E-MAILS, TO USE THE
INFORMATION, YOU HAVE TO GO
THROUGH VARIOUS KIND OF HOOPS TO
GET PERMISSION.
SO I DO THINK THAT THE
GOVERNMENT, ALTHOUGH YOU CAN
ALWAYS ARGUE ABOUT WHAT THEY
OUGHT TO DO, IT DOES OPERATE
UNDER A REGIME WHERE THEY ARE
CONTROLLED.
>> THERE HAVE BEEN SO MANY
EXAMPLES WHERE EVEN IF THOSE
PERMISSION SYSTEMS HAVE EXISTED,
THERE HAS BEEN SUCH A LACK OF
TRANSPARENCY THAT IT SHAKES OUR
FOUNDATIONAL TRUST IN THE
GOVERNMENT SAYING, HEY, IF THE
NSA HAS THIS PROGRAM, WHETHER
THEY WERE AUTHORIZED OR NOT, IT
SEEMS SHADY, IT'S ONE MORE THING
I HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT.
>> I AGREE WITH YOU, I THINK
TRANSPARENTSCY WILL BE
IMPORTANT.
ONE OF THE MISTAKES TAKES THE
GOVERNMENT MADE OVER A PERIOD OF
TIME, FOR EXAMPLE THE COURT OF
OPINION OF THE KOIRT THAT
SUPERVISORS UNDER SURVEILLANCE
IT'S KEPT CLASSIFIED.
AFTER SNOWDEN YOU KNOW DID HIS
RELEASE OF CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION, THE GOVERNMENT
STARTED TO DECLASSIFY THE
OPINIONS.
I THINK WHAT WAS PUT OUT, A, WAS
FOUGHT PARTICULARLY DAMAGING TO
NATIONAL SECURITY.
BUT FOR THE FIRST TIME PEOPLE
COULD SEE, WOW THE JUDGES ARE
REALLY DIGGING INTO THIS.
THEY COULD SEE THE REASONING OF
THE COURT AND, FRANKLY, I THINK
THE GOVERNMENT WOULD HAVE BEEN
BETTER SERVED HAD THEY PUT THIS
OUT BEFORE ANY OF THIS BUSINESS
HAPPENED.
I AGREE, I THINK A LESSON FOR
THE GOVERNMENT THE YOU HAVE TO
ASK YOURSELF IS THIS SECRECY
REALLY NECESSARY OR WILL WE
ACTUALLY GET MORE VALUE BY AT
LEAST IN A GENERALIZED WAY,
MAKING PUBLIC WHAT WE'RE DOING
TO WHAT THE RULES ARE.
>> A CORE QUESTION HERE IS THE
4th AMENDMENT.
RIGHT?
WHAT IS UNREASONABLE SEARCH AND
CEASE E SEIZURE IN THIS NEW ERA
THAT WE ARE GOING INTO?
IS MY HEART RATE INFORMATION AND
MY SLEEP HABITS, SITTING IN THE
SERVERS OF THE THIRD PARTY.
DO I HAVE CONTROL OF THAT
INFORMATION AND WHO SHOULD BE
ABLE TO TRANSACT THAT?
>> I WOULD GUESS EXACTLY THE
ISSUE WE ARE FACING.
HOW WE ARE CREATING SO MUCH
DIFFERENT DATA, WE HAVE TO
UNDERSTAND WHO GOVERNS IT.
WHAT ARE THE RULES THAT APPLY TO
THE ISSUE OF ACCESS AND THAT'S
ALREADY BEGINNING TO CHANGE.
I'LL GIVE YOU AN EXAMPLE.
YEARS AGO, MANY YEARS AGO,
ADOPTING BORDER SEARCHES, WE
WERE PROMULGATED BY THE SUPREME
COURT.
WHICH CROSS THE BORDER TO COME
INTO THE U.S., BORDER OFFICIALS
ARE ABLE SEARCH ANYTHING YOU
CARRY WITH YOU.
YOU HAVE A LIMIT TO WHAT YOU CAN
PURCHASE REPORT INTO THE U.S.
THAT WAS APPLIED TO LAPTOPS AND
OTHER REPOSITORY DATA, BECAUSE
YOU ARE BRINGING IT INTO THE
UNDERSTAND K. NOW VERY RECENTLY
THE ISSUE WAS RAISED WHAT DO YOU
DO, FOR EXAMPLE, THE SMART HOME
WHICH IS CONNECTED TO THE CLOUD.
SO IF YOU ARE ABLE OPEN UP THE
PHONE AND SEARCH THE PHONE, YOU
ARET NOT ONLY GETTING ON THE
PHONE, ARE GETTING WHAT MAY BE
SITTING ON AMAZON SERVERS
SOMEWHERE IN THE UNITED STATES.
IT WOULD BE AS IF I SEARCHED YOU
WHEN YOU CAME INTO COUNTRY.
AND THE SUPREME COURT CAN
ACCOUNT FOR THE SHEER VOLUME OF
MATERIAL THAT IS NOW AVAILABLE
ON A PHONE OR A LOOPTOP.
>> I WANT TO ASK ALSO ABOUT
UPCOMING ELECTIONS, ARE THERE IS
TWO LEVELS.
ARE STATE SYSTEMS IN THE UNITED
STATES SECURE ENOUGH?
>> TWO LEVELS, THE
INFRASTRUCTURE, THAT IS THE
VOTING MACHINES AN VOTER
REGISTRATION ROLLS AND
TABULATION.
I THINK IT'S VERY UNEASY,
CONGRESS IS TRYING TO GET MORE
MONEY, THE DEPARTMENT OF
HOMELAND SECURITY IS WORKING
WITH SOME OF THE STATES THAT
UPGRADE THEIR SECURITY OF THE
INFRASTRUCTURE.
AND THERE ARE SOME THINGS THAT I
HAVE BEEN INVOLVED IN THE
COMMISSION ON ELECTION INTEGRITY
WHERE WE ARE TRYING TO PROMOTE
THAT.
THE LARGER ISSUE, THOUGH, IS
WHAT THEY CALL INFORMATION
OPERATIONS.
IT'S THE USE BY FOREIGN
GOVERNMENTS, LIKE THE RUSSIANS
OR EVEN FRANKLY BY PEOPLE IN OUR
OWN COUNTRY OF TOOLS DESIGNED TO
MANIPULATE PUBLIC OPINION AND
CREATE THERE UNITY AND EVEN
SUPPRESS VOTING BY PROPAGATING
STORIES OR MAGNIIFYING
DISTURBING STORIES, ALL TO PLAY
WITH EMOTIONS.
THERE ARE SOME THINGS YOU CAN DO
TO MITIGATE THAT, PARTICULARLY
WHEN HAVE YOU FOREIGN GOVERNMENT
INVOLVED.
BUT AGAIN, SOME OF THIS IS GOING
TO REQUIRE THE HARD WORK AND THE
EDUCATION OF THE PEOPLE ABOUT
HOW TO BE CRITICAL THINKERS.
THIS IS ABOUT TO GET MORE
CHALLENGING, BECAUSE WE ARE NOW
ON THE VERGE OF WHAT THEY CALL
FAKES.
WHICH IS THE ABILITY TO CREATE
AUDIO AND VIDEO THAT IS
COMPLETELY FABRICATED THAT MAKES
IT SEEM LIKE A REAL PERSON IS
SAYING SMCHLTH AND IF THAT
STARTS TO GET USED AGAINST
CANDIDATES, FOR EXAMPLE, WILL
YOU REALLY HAVE STRESS ON THE
NOTION OF DETERMINING WHAT THE
TRUTH IS.
>> WHAT HAPPENS TO OUR
PROFESSION?
>> WELL, A BIG PIECE OF THIS IS
ACTUALLY BEING PUT ON
JOURNALISM.
HOW DO YOU MEASURE AND DETEBT
WHETHER SOMETHING IS PALS?
HOW DO YOU MAKE SURE YOU DON'T
GET CAUGHT UP IN THE --
>> ON THE COMPETITION FOR AGAIN
ZSA?
>> THE COMPETITION FOR CLIFFS
WHICH DRIVES THE BEHAVIOR YOU
ARE TRYING TO FIGHT AGAINST.
REINJECTING AN ELEMENT OF
PROFESSIONALISM AND JUDGMENT IN
THE WAY EDITORIAL DECISIONS ARE
MADE.
I THINK THERE IS AN IMPORTANT
PART OF PRESERVING OUR
DEMOCRACY.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> A DIFFICULT CHALLENGE AHEAD.
BEFORE WE GO, REMEMBER TO TUNE
IN TOMORROW WHEN WE WILL HAVE A
SPECIAL PROGRAM ON HUMANITY'S
BIGGEST TRIAL, THAT IS CLIMATE
CHANGE.
I WILL SPEAK WITH THE WASHINGTON
GOVERNOR, MAKING IT THE CENTER
OF A POSSIBLE PRESIDENTIAL
CAMPAIGN AND I'LL TALK TO THE
FLAFR GAMES BALOG, WHO HAS
DEVOTED HIS LIFE, HE HAS A NEW
FILM TO HUMAN ELEMENTS.
THANK YOU U THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AMANPOUR AND COMPANY ON
PBS AND JOIN US AGAIN NEXT TIME.
♪♪