"A.M. JOY", LIVE FROM NEW
ORLEANS.
WELL, THIS WEEK ON AMERICA'S
BIRTHDAY, KNOWN AS INDEPENDENCE
DAY OR SIMPLY JULY 4, DONALD
TRUMP THREW HIMSELF A PARTY.
EVER SINCE HE SAW THAT THE
FRENCH PRESIDENT HAS A PARADE,
IT'S CALLED BASTILLE DAY AND THE
DICTATOR OF NORTH KOREA HAS A
PARADE, IT'S CALLED
AUTHORITARIANISM, AND THAT THEY
GET TO HAVE TANKS AND PEOPLE
MARCHING IN FRONT OF THEM AND
SALUTING THEM, AND ALL OF THAT
STUFF, HE'S WANTED TO HAVE ONE
TOO.
HE TRIED TO CO-OP OTHER HOLIDAYS
LIKE VETERANS DAY AND MEMORIAL
DAY, BUT THE ADULTS IN THE
MILITARY KEPT PUSHING HIM BACK.
NO MORE.
DONALD TRUMP FINALLY GOT HIS
SPECIAL DONALD TRUMP PARADE,
ROLLING TANKS DOWN THE STREETS
OF YOUR CAPITAL, FLYING AIR
FORCE PLANES OVER HIS HEAD WHILE
HE GAVE AN ODD SPEECH ABOUT THE
AIRPORTS, THE CONTINENTAL
CONGRESS TOOK CONTROL OF DURING
THE REVOLUTIONARY WAR?
>> IN JUNE OF 1775, THE
CONTINENTAL CONGRESS CREATED A
UNIFIED ARMY OUT OF THE
REVOLUTIONARY FORCES ENCAMPED
AROUND BOSTON AND NEW YORK.
AND NAMED AFTER THE GREAT GEORGE
WASHINGTON COMMANDER IN CHIEF.
THE CONTINENTAL ARMY SUFFERED A
BITTER WINTER OF VALLEY FORGE,
FOUND GLORY ACROSS THE WATERS OF
THE DELAWARE, AND SEIZED VICTORY
FROM CORN WALLACE OF YORK TOWN.
IT RAN THE RAMPARTS IT TOOK OVER
THE AIRPORTS, IT DID EVERYTHING
IT HAD TO DO AND AT FORT
McHENDRY UNDER THE ROCKETS RED
GLARE, IT HAD NOTHING BUT
VICTORY.
>> OKAY.
I'M SURE YOU KNOW THIS ALREADY
BECAUSE YOU PAID ATTENTION IN
SCHOOL BUT JUST SO THAT IT'S
SAID, THE CONTINENTAL ARMY WAS
NOT NAMED AFTER GEORGE
WASHINGTON.
THERE WAS NO AIR TRAVEL DURING
THE REVOLUTIONARY WAR.
AIRPLANES WEREN'T EVEN INVENTED
UNTIL 1903, AND THE BATTLE AT
FORT McHENDRY HAPPENED DURING
THE WAR OF 1812.
DETAILS.
IN THE END, FOR MILLIONS OF YOUR
TAX DOLLARS, THIS IS ACTUALLY
WHAT DONALD TRUMP GOT.
>> ON THIS DAY, 243 YEARS AGO,
OUR FOUNDING FATHERS PLEDGED
THEIR LIVES, THEIR FORTUNES AND
THEIR SACRED HONOR TO DECLARE
INDEPENDENCE AND DEFEND OUR GOD
GIVEN RIGHTS.
>> NOT AN AMERICAN PRESIDENT BUT
WHAT LOOKS LIKE AN AUTHORITARIAN
LEADER, FESTOONED BY HIS
MILITARY AND MAKING A SHOW OF
FORCE TO, WELL, IT'S NOT REALLY
CLEAR WHO BECAUSE DONALD TRUMP
ACTUALLY REALLY LIKES DICTATORS.
JOINING ME NOW IS PRESIDENT O
AND CEO OF LATINO.
CRAIG UNGER, VANITY FAIR
CONTRIBUTOR, AND AUTHOR OF HOUSE
OF TRUMP, HOUSE OF PUTIN, AND
REPRESENTATIVE TED LOU, DEMOCRAT
FROM CALIFORNIA, AND A MEMBER OF
THE FOREIGN AFFAIRS AND
JUDICIARY COMMITTEES.
I WANT TO GO TO YOU FIRST,
CONGRESSMAN, WHAT DID YOU MAKE
OF IT, WATCHING AN AMERICAN
PRESIDENT DO THIS THING THAT TOM
NICHOLS, WHO IS A SOVIET, EXPERT
ON THE HISTORY OF THE SOVIET
UNION AND OF THAT REGION,
DESCRIBED AS LOOKING LIKE AN OLD
SOVIET KIND OF, YOU KNOW,
PARADE.
>> THANK YOU, JOY FOR YOUR
QUESTION.
LET ME JUST FIRST SAY THAT
NATURAL DISASTER LIKE
EARTHQUAKES CAN STRIKE AT ANY
TIME AND I URGE TO BE PREPARED
WITH SUPPLIES AND A SAFETY PLAN.
TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTION, ONE OF
THE BIG PROBLEMS WITH TRUMP'S
JULY 4th EVENT IS IT WAS A
CAMPAIGN EVENT PAID FOR BY THE
AMERICAN TAXPAYER.
NOT ONLY DID HE DIVERT MILLIONS
OF DOLLARS TO THIS EVENT, HE HAD
THE REPUBLICAN NATIONAL
COMMITTEE GIVE OUT PASSES, VIP
PASSES TO MAJOR DONORS.
THAT WAS OUTRAGEOUS.
THAT WAS A VIOLATION OF OUR
ETHICS AND HE MADE A MOCKERY OF
OUR INDEPENDENCE DAY.
>> THANK YOU FOR MENTIONING
WHAT'S GOING ON IN YOUR STATE.
WE JUST SAW TWO NATURAL DISASTER
IN THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA, SO
THIS IS A TIME WHEN THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT ACTUALLY HAS
PRIORITIES THAT ARE IMPORTANT
THAT WE SHOULD BE SPENDING MONEY
ON, THINGS LIKE MAKING SURE THAT
STATES ARE READY FOR NATURAL
DISASTER LIKE YOU JUST SAW IN
YOUR STATE.
WHEN YOU SEE THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES DIVERTING
MONEY SO HE CAN HAVE PLANES FLY
OVER HIM, RATHER THAN SPENDING
THE MONEY ON IMPORTANT THINGS
LIKE THAT, OR MAYBE UNCAGING
CHILDREN, WHICH HE'S ALSO DOING
IN THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA AND
ARIZONA AND OTHER PLACES, AS A
MEMBER OF CONGRESS, IS THERE
SOMETHING THAT YOU PLAN TO DO
ABOUT THAT.
THIS DOES SEEM LIKE A TREMENDOUS
WASTE OF MONEY.
>> MEMBERS OF CONGRESS CAN'T USE
OFFICIAL RESOURCES TO
PARTICIPATE IN A PARADE.
IN THIS CASE, TRUMP DIVERTS
$2.5 MILLION OF NATIONAL PARK
FEES TO PAY FOR HIS PARTY, AND
I'VE ASKED THE FEDERAL ELECTION
COMMISSION TO LOOK INTO THIS
BECAUSE HOW CAN YOU HAVE ALL OF
THIS TAXPAYER MONEY DO THIS
EVENT AND HAVE THE REPUBLICAN
NATIONAL COMMITTEE BE INVOLVED
HANDING OUT VIP PASSES TO THE
MAJOR DONORS.
>> YEAH, AND BESIDES THAT, I
WANT TO GO TO YOU CRAIG UNGER,
YOU HAVE WRITTEN A LOT ABOUT
DONALD TRUMP, HIS MAFIA SORT OF
RELATIONSHIPS THAT HE HAS HAD
THROUGHOUT HIS CAREER,
PARTICULARLY WHEN IT COMES TO
RUSSIA.
THIS IS WHAT MICHAEL McFALL, THE
FORMER U.S. AMBASSADOR TO RUSSIA
TWEETED AFTER DONALD TRUMP'S
WEIRD PARADE.
HE SAID I KNEW THIS WAS COMING,
TWEET FROM JULIA DAVIS NEWS,
RUSSIA STATE TV IS OBSESSIVELY
BASHING TRUMP'S LOW ENERGY WEAK
PARADE WITH RUSTY TANKS, THE
HOSTS LOL AT TRUMP'S CLAIM'S,
THERE'S YOUR CITY UPON A HILL, A
WORLD LEADER AND MARTIANS HAVE
BEEN DEFEATED.
DONALD TRUMP NOT ONLY WASTED
AMERICA'S MONEY TO MAKE HIMSELF
A CAMPAIGN COMMERCIAL BUT ALSO
HAS SUBJECTED THE UNITED STATES
TO MOCKERY BECAUSE REAL
DICTATORSHIPS KNOW WHAT A
DICTATOR PARADE IS SUPPOSED TO
LOOK LIKE, CRAIG.
>> AT LEAST SOMETIMES THEY GET
THEIR FACTS STRAIGHT, AND I
MEAN, IT'S INTERESTING THAT IF
THE RUSSIAN STATE TV IS GOING
AFTER TRUMP, THAT DOESN'T HAPPEN
WITHOUT VLADIMIR PUTIN'S SAY SO.
IT'S ALSO INTERESTING, THE CLIP
YOU SHOWED, THE NUMBER OF
HISTORICAL ERRORS IN IT IS JUST
EXTRAORDINARY, AND THE WHITE
HOUSE HAS AN OFFICE OF SPEECH
WRITING WITH LOTS OF RESEARCHERS
AND INTERNS AND THEY FACT CHECK
THINGS, AND THERE ARE ONLY THREE
POSSIBILITIES FOR THAT LEVEL OF
STUPIDITY TO TAKE PLACE.
ONE IS THAT THAT OFFICE IS
COMPLETELY FILLED WITH PEOPLE
WITH ROOM TEMPERATURE IQ, THE
OTHER IS THAT ALL THE PROCEDURES
HAVE FALLEN APART, AND THEY
DON'T EXIST ANYMORE, AND THE
THIRD POSSIBILITY IS IT'S
SPRAYING FROM THE BRAIN OF
DONALD TRUMP, AND THAT IS
DEEPLY, DEEPLY DISTURBING.
>> YEAH, THERE'S A LOT ABOUT IT
THAT'S DISTURBING LONNIE, I'M
GOING TO GO TO YOU ON THIS, I'M
GLAD YOU'RE HERE TO HAVE A
HISTORICAL CONTEXT.
DONALD TRUMP ADMIRES DICTATOR
SHIPS AROUND THE WORLD.
ALL OF THE MEDIA IS HIS VERSION
OF THE BASTILLE DAY CEREMONY.
I POINTED OUT EARLIER THIS WEEK,
THE WHOLE BASTILLE DAY THING IS
ABOUT SENDING A MESSAGE TO
DICTATORS.
THAT'S WHAT THE WHOLE BASTILLE
DAY IS ABOUT.
THAT'S CLEARLY NOT WHAT THIS IS.
DONALD TRUMP LIKES DICTATORS.
WHAT WAS THE MESSAGE THAT YOU
THINK CAME OUT OF WHAT DONALD
TRUMP DID THIS WEEK?
>> IT WAS GRANDIOSITY AND
SELF-INFLATION, AND SO ONE OF
THE THINGS, I THINK, THAT'S
SIGNIFICANT HERE IS THAT THE
UNITED STATES, AT LEAST IN
THEORY, IS SUPPOSED TO OPERATE
ON THE DOCTRINE THAT WE ARE A
NATION OF LAWS, THAT NO ONE IS
ABOVE THE LAW, AND THAT THE
CONSTITUTION IS THE FUNDAMENTAL
AUTHORITY.
THAT IS A DIFFERENT POSITION,
FUNDAMENTALLY DIFFERENT POSITION
THAN A STATE IN WHICH THE
PERSONALITY OR THE AUTHORITARIAN
LEADER IS THE HEAD OF ALL
INTEREST AND IDEAS WITHIN THE
STATE, AND SO WHAT DONALD TRUMP
DID WAS ESSENTIALLY HIJACK THIS
IDEA AND TURN IT INTO SOMETHING
THAT WAS SUPPOSED TO GLORIFY
ITSELF.
IT'S AN INTERESTING PARADOX
HERE, WHICH IS THAT SEVERAL
YEARS AGO, I DID A FULL BRIGHT
FELLOWSHIP AND SPENT AN ENTIRE
SEMESTER IN MOSCOW, TEACHING AT
MOSCOW STATE UNIVERSITY AND AT
THE END OF THE SEMESTER, THERE
WAS THE MAY 9th CELEBRATION.
ANYBODY WHO HAS BEEN TO RUSSIA
OR KNOWS, YOU KNOW, ABOUT THEIR
HISTORY POST WORLD WAR II, MAY
9th IS A GIGANTIC CELEBRATION
THAT HAPPENS EACH YEAR SOMEWHERE
BETWEEN THE FOURTH OF JULY AND
NEW YEAR'S AND IT IS A
RECOGNITION OF THE SOVIET DEFEAT
OF THE NAZI THREAT, AN THREAT IN
WORLD WAR II.
IT'S HUGE.
I WAS THERE FOR THE PARADE AND
THERE'S THIS COMPLETE PROCESSION
OF MILITARY VEHICLES.
THEIR MISSILES, TANKS, ARMORED
VEHICLES, THEIR JEEPS AND IT
LOOKS LIKE AN ARMY AMASSING FOR
AN INVASION.
SOMEONE TURNS TO ME AND SAYS DO
YOU DO THE SAME THING IN THE
UNITED STATES ON THE FOURTH OF
JULY.
I SAID, NO, THIS WOULD NEVER
HAPPEN IN THE UNITED STATES
BECAUSE THEY, IN THE UNITED
STATES BELIEVER THERE SHOULD BE
A REALLY CLEAR DISTINCTION
BETWEEN CIVILIAN AUTHORITY AND
MILITARY MIGHT AND THAT OUR
AUTHORITY IS SUPPOSED TO, AT
LEAST IN THEORY, STEM FROM OUR
LAWS AND OUR MORAL BELIEVES.
AND WHAT DONALD TRUMP DID WAS
ESSENTIALLY INVERT THAT TO
CREATE IT AS THE KIND OF
SATIRICAL, ALMOST, EMULATION OF
SOMETHING THAT HE SEES IN
VLADIMIR PUTIN, WE SHOULD
RECOGNIZE THIS AS THE
ANTIDEMOCRATIC MOVEMENT THAT IT
ACTUALLY WAS.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, THAT IS AN
EXCELLENT POINT.
HE TALKED ABOUT THE FACT THAT
TRUMP TRIED TO MAKE HIMSELF LOOK
BIG FROM THIS PIECE.
IT WAS CLEAR FROM THE BEGINNING
THAT INDEPENDENCE MEANT NOTHING
MORE THAN A MADE FOR TELEVISION
EVENT AND AN EGO MESSAGE.
IT INVOKED MOCKERY.
THERE'S A CARTOON THAT'S DRAWN
ON WHAT AIRPLANES WOULD LOOK
LIKE DURING THE REVOLUTIONARY
WAR.
IT'S BEN FRANKLIN ATTACHED TO
TWO KITES AND THIS IS BY
SOMEBODY I KNOW, THE GREAT
NATALIE JOHNSON WHO DREW THAT.
HERE'S THE REALITY, DONALD TRUMP
IT SEEMS WANTS TO BE SEEN AS
THIS BIG MAN, RIGHT, HE WANTS TO
BE SEEN AS THIS GRAND LEADER OF
THIS GREAT MILITARY BUT WHAT HE
ACTUALLY CAN ACCOMPLISH THROUGH
HIS OWN, YOU KNOW, THE QUALITY
OF THE STAFF THAT HE HAS AROUND
HIM IS HE CAN'T DO THAT.
THE REALITY IS EVEN IN THE CASE
OF RUSSIA, WHICH NOW IS AN
ADVERSARY OF THE UNITED STATES,
DURING WORLD WAR II, THEY WERE
FIGHTING THE NAZIS.
IF THEY'RE DOING A BIG
CELEBRATION, TALKING ABOUT
DEFEATING THE NAZI EMPIRE,
THEY'RE SENDING A MESSAGE AGAIN
TO DICTATORS.
THERE ARE TWO KINDS OF PARADES,
THAT AND ONE IN NORTH KOREA.
TRUMP IS TRYING TO DO IT.
HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW HOW.
>> OR REALLY WHY.
>> WE ARE THE LARGEST MILITARY
OPERATION IN THE WORLD.
WE DON'T HAVE TO SHOW THAT TYPE
OF DISPLAY OF FORCE BECAUSE THE
WORLD ALREADY KNOWS IT AND WHAT
I FOUND SO DISAPPOINTING WHEN IT
CAME TO JULY 4th IS JULY 4th IS
TO COMMEMORATE OUR ROOTS AS
AMERICANS, THE FACT THAT WE FLED
DIFFERENT COUNTRIES HERE, AND
RECOGNIZE THAT, OUR DNA IS WE'RE
A NATION OF IMMIGRANTS AND WE
HAVE STRENGTH AND DON'T HAVE TO
SHOW MILITARY MIGHT BECAUSE THE
WORLD KNOWS IT, AND WHAT DONALD
TRUMP DID WAS A SAD DISPLAY.
HE DIDN'T HAVE THE COURAGE TO
JOIN THE MILITARY WHEN HIS CARD
WAS UP.
HE DEFERRED IT ON BONE SPURS AND
BASICALLY NOT ONLY DETERIORATES
THE FLAG BUT ALSO THE MEANING OF
WHAT MEANS TO BE AMERICAN AND
JULY 4th AND COME TOGETHER AS A
NATION.
THE REASONS PRESIDENTS DON'T
MAKE IT ABOUT THEM IS BECAUSE
IT'S ONE COUNTRY, UNDER ONE FLAG
IN UNISON.
IT'S NOT SUPPOSED TO BE
PARTISAN.
HE CREATED A CAMPAIGN RALLY,
TRYING TO DIFFERENTIATE US AND
DIVIDE US.
WHAT I THINK IS BEAUTIFUL IS YOU
SAW FAMILIES ON THE LAWN SAYING
I'M APOLITICAL AND I'M HERE TO
SHARE IT WITH FAMILIES.
WE KNOW WHAT WE ARE.
WE KNOW WHO WE ARE, AND WE KNOW
WE DO IT WITH JUSTICE.
THE FACT THAT HE CAN DO THIS IN
THE BACKDROP OF CAGING CHILDREN,
THAT IS NOT WHO WE ARE.
AND THE MORE WE CAN STAND STRONG
TO VALUES, DESPITE THE OPERATION
IN OUR HISTORY, WE HAVE TO MAKE
SURE THAT WE ARE CLEAR MINDED ON
WHAT IT MEANS TO BE AMERICAN AND
FAIR AND JUST.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT WHAT YOU
SAW, DONALD TRUMP MADE US LOOK
STRONGER AND WEAKER AS A
COUNTRY.
>> ABSOLUTELY WEAKER.
THE WORST PART OF IT IS THAT HAD
THIS NOT BEEN AN INEPT DISPLAY
OF PSEUDO AUTHORITARIANISM, WE
STILL WOULD HAVE LOOKED WEAKER.
IF HE HAD DOWN THIS CORRECTLY,
IN AIR QUOTES CORRECTLY, WE
WOULD HAVE LOOKED WEAKER.
NOW WE LOOK DOUBLY WEAKER,
BECAUSE IT'S A POOR IMITATION OF
WHAT IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE IN
THE FIRST PLACE.
>> WHEN THE RUSSIANS LOOK AT US,
THEY ARE LAUGHING AT US.
IS HE A SUBJECT OF MOCKERY TO
THEM.
>> I THINK HE IS SUBJECT TO
MOCKERY, THE IMAGES THAT COME
AWAY IS WE HAVE CONCENTRATION
CAMPS ON THE BORDER, TANKS BY
THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL.
THERE WAS AN PIECE TO THE
"WASHINGTON POST," THE
ARCHITECTURE IS ABOUT
RECONCILIATION, IT'S ABOUT THE
LINCOLN MEMORIAL, OUR ORIGINAL
SIN WAS SLAVERY.
THE CIVIL WAR, AND THIS IS WHERE
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO HAVE
RECONCILIATION, AND INSTEAD
TODAY WE HAVE IMAGES OF TANKS
AND THE WHOLE CRISIS AT THE
BORDER.
>> I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU THE
LAST WORD, CONGRESSMAN.
AS A PERSON WHO DID SERVE,
UNLIKE DONALD TRUMP, WHEN YOU
SAW TANKS ROLLING DOWN THE
NATION'S CAPITOL, YOUR THOUGHTS
WERE WHAT?
>> HAVING SERVED IN THE ACTIVE
DUTY IN THE MILITARY, WE HAVE
BEEN TRAINED NOT TO PARTICIPATE
IN PARTISAN CAMPAIGN EVENTS.
THERE'S A DIRECTIVE THAT
PROHIBITS MILITARY MEMBERS FROM
SHOWING UP IN UNIFORM AT A
CAMPAIGN RALLY.
THIS WAS A MASSIVE TAX FUNDED
CAMPAIGN RALLY, HANDING OUT VIP
PASSES, IT ERODED WHAT SHOULD BE
A NONPARTISAN MILITARY AND THAT
WAS SAD AND DISAPPOINTING.
>> THANK YOU ALL FOR BEING HERE
AND SENDING OUT GOOD THOUGHTS TO
YOUR STATE CONGRESSMAN, JILANI
COBB, CRAIG UNGER, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
>>> PEOPLE LOCKED IN CAGES ON
THE SOUTHERN BOARD, MORE ON THAT
NEXT.
CAGES ON
THE SOUTHERN BOARD, MORE ON THAT
NEXT
Coach! It's kinda hard to see
the ball.
I've been there.
I had a TV service with hardly
any sports in 4K.
Couldn't see any of the quality
details.
I switched to DIRECTV, now I get
the most live sports in 4K.
So how does that help me?
It really doesn't.
I don't know why I told you
that. Go get 'em sport!
Live sports that aren't in 4K
are just kinda TV.
Don't just kinda TV. DIRECTV
Don't have 4K? Call
1.855.WATCH.4K and ask for it
today.
UNCONSCIONABLE.
NO CHILD SHOULD EVER BE
SEPARATED FROM THEIR PARENT.
>> THE MOTHERS, THE ABUELAS, THE
TIAS, THE MADRES, WHO I SAT WITH
WHO WE WANT OPENLY IN OUR ARMS.
>> I'LL NEVER FORGET THE IMAGE
OF BEING IN A CELL AND SEEING 15
WOMEN TEARS COMING DOWN THEIR
FACES AS THEY TALKED ABOUT BEING
SEPARATED FROM THEIR CHILDREN,
ABOUT HAVING NO RUNNING WATER.
>> IN FACT, ONE OF THE WOMEN
SAID THAT SHE WAS TOLD BY AN
AGENT TO DRINK WATER OUT OF THE
TOILET.
>> THIS WEEK DEMOCRATIC
LAWMAKERS ONCE AGAIN SAW FOR
THEMSELVES THE SHAMEFUL
CONDITIONS THAT MIGRANT CHILDREN
AND ADULTS HAVE BEEN FORCED TO
LIVE, SPECIFICALLY AT A
DETENTION FACILITY IN CLINT,
TEXAS.
CONDITIONS AT THE DEPARTMENT OF
HOMELAND SECURITY'S INSPECTOR
GENERAL CONFIRMED IN A REPORT
THIS WEEK.
LET ME READ TO YOU SOME OF THE
FINDINGS, QUOTE, CHILDREN AT
THREE OF THE FIVE BORDER PATROL
FACILITIES THAT WE VISITED HAD
NO ACCESS TO SHOWERS.
AT THESE FACILITIES CHILDREN HAD
LIMITED ACCESS TO A CHANGE OF
CLOTHES, BORDER PATROL HAD FEW
SPARE CLOTHES AND LAUNDRY
FACILITIES WHILE ALL FACILITIES
HAD INFANT FORMULA, DIAPERS,
BABY WIPES, JUICE AND SNACKS FOR
CHILDREN, TWO FACILITIES HAD NOT
PROVIDED CHILDREN ACCESS TO HOT
MEALS.
BUT CUSTOMS AND BORDER PATROL
WAS SO DESPERATE TO DISPEL THESE
FIRSTHAND ACCOUNTS FROM
LAWMAKERS AND ACTIVISTS THAT ONE
OF IT CHIEFS FILMED A VIDEO
SHOWING A SUPPLY ROOM WITH AN
ABUNDANCE OF CLOTHING AND
SUPPLIES, AND A CLEAN AREA, 300
MILES AWAY IN ARIZONA.
BACK WITH ME, MARIA THERESA
KUMAR, AND ANDREA PITZER AUTHOR
OF ONE LONG NIGHT.
AND LAURA, DIRECTOR OF
IMMIGRANTS RIGHTS AT COLUMBIA
LAW SCHOOL AND A LAWYER WHO HAS
VISITED DETENTION CENTERS FOR
THE LAST 10 YEARS.
LAURA, I WANT TO PLAY FOR YOU A
LITTLE BIT, A VIDEO THAT WAS
OBTAINED OF A 12-YEAR-OLD GIRL,
A 12-YEAR-OLD MIGRANT, HER
ACCOUNT OF BEING DETAINED FOR
TWO WEEKS.
IT'S IN SPANISH FOR THOSE OF YOU
WHO ARE WATCHING.
YOU'LL HAVE TO READ THE SUB
TITLES.
[ SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
]
AND LAURA, WE HAVE HEARD STORIES
OF LITTLE KIDS BEING FORCED TO
TAKE CARE OF OTHER LITTLE KIDS.
CHILDREN SLEEPING ON THE GROUND
IN NOTHING BUT A DIAPER.
CHILDREN SAYING THEY HAVE ONE
MEAL A DAY.
IS THIS LEGAL?
>> NO, THIS IS ABSOLUTELY NOT
LEGAL.
FEDERAL LAW PROVIDES FOR
PROTECTIONS FOR CHILDREN IN
FEDERAL IMMIGRATION CUSTODY.
THE 1997 FLORES SETTLEMENT
AGREEMENT REQUIRES THAT THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT PROVIDE SAFE
AND SANITARY CONDITIONS FOR
CHILDREN IN ITS CUSTODY.
A LAW FROM 2008 WHICH WAS PASSED
WITH UNANIMOUS BIPARTISAN
SUPPORT AND SIGNED BY PRESIDENT
GEORGE W. BUSH SAYS THAT
CHILDREN MUST NOT BE DETAINED BY
CUSTOMS AND BORDER PATROL FOR
ANY LONGER THAN 72 HOURS.
THE CONDITIONS THAT WE'RE
LEARNING ABOUT, WHAT WE HEAR,
WHAT I SMELLED WHEN I WAS AT
THESE FACILITIES, IT IS
UNLAWFUL, AND ILLEGAL.
>> AND THEN, LAURA, THIS IS WHAT
I HAVE NOT UNDERSTOOD AND I'M
GOING TO GO TO YOU FIRST, AND
THEN MARIA THERESA KUMAR BECAUSE
WE HAVE BEEN TALKING ABOUT WHY
THEY MIGHT BE DOING THIS.
THEY'RE HOLDING KIDS FOR 50
DAYS, 40 DAYS, 30 DAYS, ALMOST
AS IF THE RANSOM, THEY CAN'T
LEAVE.
HOW CAN THEY GET AWAY WITH IT IF
IT'S ILLEGAL.
>> IT IS ILLEGAL AND WHAT'S
IMPORTANT TO KNOW IS THAT MOST
OF THESE CHILDREN HAVE FAMILY
MEMBERS IN THE UNITED STATES WHO
ARE DESPERATE TO HAVE THEIR
CHILDREN BACK.
80% OF CHILDREN RELEASED FROM
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT ARE
HOUSED AND CARED FOR AND LOVED
FOR BY THEIR OWN FAMILY MEMBERS.
WE NEED IMMEDIATE CONGRESSIONAL
OVERSIGHT AND PRESSURE ON THIS
ADMINISTRATION TO RELEASE
CHILDREN FROM DETENTION AS
QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE AND WHILE
CHILDREN ARE DETAINED THEY MUST
BE TREATED HUMANELY.
>> YOU KNOW, MARIA THERESA
KUMAR, I HAVE TO GO TO YOU ON
THIS.
WE HAVE BEEN DOWN THERE.
YOU HAVE BEEN THERE MUCH MORE
THAN I HAVE.
LAURA HAS BEEN THERE.
I'M NOT A LAWYER.
IT STRIKES ME AS COMPLETELY
ILLEGAL TO HOLD CHILDREN IN THIS
MANNER WHEN AS LAURA SAID, THEY
HAVE FAMILY TO GO TO.
DONALD TRUMP SAYS THAT'S CATCH
AND RELEASE, HE'S NOT DOING IT.
WHY IN YOUR VIEW ARE THEY
HOLDING THESE CHILDREN?
IS IT THE MONEY THAT THEY'RE
MAKING, I MEAN IT'S 750 BUCKS A
DAY TO HOLD KIDS IN THESE CAMPS.
IS IT STRAIGHT MONEY, WHY ARE
THEY NOT LETTING THEM GO?
>> I THINK THERE'S A COUPLE OF
THINGS.
ONE, IT'S POLITICAL FODDER, IT
SHOWS THAT HE IS THE STRONG
FISTED PERSON MAKING SURE
THEY'RE TRYING TO USE THIS AS A
DETERRENT.
HE DIDN'T COME UP WITH THIS.
IT'S STEVE MILLER, HIS SENIOR
ADVISER WITH HIS FINGER PRINTS
ALL OVER IT.
IT'S POLITICAL FODDER FOR HIS
BASE.
HE'S BEING TOUGH AND IT'S THE
PARENTS' FAULT HE CAME HERE.
TWO, THERE'S A LOT OF MONEY TO
BE MAID.
THE PRIVATE DETENTION
FACILITIES, THE FOR PROFIT
DETENTION FACILITIES, STOCK
PRICES WENT ON THE RISE.
THE CHIEF OF STAFF, THE FORMER
CHIEF OF STAFF JOHN KELLY WHO
ADVISED PRESIDENT TRUMP AND WAS
HEAD OF THE DHS, HE WAS ONE OF
THE ARCHITECTURES OF THIS.
GUESS WHERE JOHN KELLY IS NOW.
HE IS NOW ON THE BOARD OF
ADVISERS TO ONE OF THE LARGEST
DETENTION FOR PROFIT FACILITIES.
HE HAS GONE DOWN TO HOMESTEAD,
IN FLORIDA, HOUSING 3,200
MINORS.
PRESIDENT OBAMA PROCESSED
INDIVIDUALS AND DEPORTED THEM.
THIS PRESIDENT HAS LITTLE
INTENTION OF DEPORTING THEM.
THESE CHILDREN ARE NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE IN CUSTODY MORE THAN 72
DAYS.
IN SOME CASES, THEY ARE THERE
FOR MONTHS, IN SOME CASES,
ALMOST A YEAR, AND IT'S CLEAR
THE ONLY WAY YOU DO IT IS ENSURE
SOMEONE IS MAKING A LOT OF
PROFIT, AND YOU DO IT AWAY FROM
THE CAMERAS, AWAY FROM THE
AMERICAN PUBLIC AND YOU DO IT
ALMOST IN SECRET.
THE FACT THAT THIS IS BASICALLY,
YOU HAVE SOME I.C.E. AGENTS
COMING OUT AND ANONYMOUSLY
SHOWING PICTURES OF WHAT IS
HAPPENING IN THE FACILITIES.
THEY'RE TRYING TO ALSO, YOU
KNOW, RING THE RED LIGHT OF THIS
IS NOT NORMAL.
THIS IS ILLEGAL, AND WE NEED THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE TO STAND UP FOR
IT.
THE FACT THAT THE UNITED NATIONS
HAVE DECLARED THAT THE UNITED
STATES IS IN VIOLATION OF
CHILDREN'S HUMAN RIGHTS SHOULD
BE SCREAMING AT THE TOP OF THE
LUNGS OF EVERY SINGLE AMERICAN
SAYING THIS IS NOT WHO WE ARE.
THIS IS WHAT WE ACTUALLY STAND
FOR.
>> ANDREA, I MEAN, WE HAVE HAD A
WHOLE BUNCH OF PEOPLE GETTING
UPSET AND DEBATING OVER WHAT YOU
CALL THESE CAMPS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE YOU WOULD
CALL IT OTHER THAN CONCENTRATION
CAMPS.
THEY WON'T LET THEM GO, SEEM TO
BE DISPLAYING MISERY TO
ENTERTAIN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS THEY'RE
TRYING TO SHOW THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE.
THEY SEEM TO WANT US TO KNOW
THEY'RE DOING THIS TO THESE
KIDS.
WE HAD A YOUNG MAN WHO WAS
ALLEGEDLY SHAMED.
THIS ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW, THEY
HUNG A SIGN ON HIM, SAYING I
LIKE MEN IN SPANISH AND PUT A
SIGN ON HIM TO TRY TO HUMILIATE
HIM.
THIS REMINDS ME OF THE WAY WE
BEHAVED AT ABU GRAVE WHERE IT
WAS TRYING TO DISPLAY THE
MOCKERY OF THESE PEOPLE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT'S GOING
ON HERE AND NO ONE IS STOPPING
IT.
YOUR THOUGHTS, ANDREA.
>> LOOK, IT'S NO SURPRISE THAT
THERE ARE ECHOES OF PRIOR CAMP
SYSTEMS IN GOING BACK MORE THAN
A HUNDRED YEARS IN WHAT WE'RE
SEEING ON THE BORDER TODAY.
THE TURN OF THE 20th CENTURY,
EMILY HOB HOUSE WENT DOWN TO
SOUTHERN AFRICA AND WERE SHOCKED
THAT THE BRITISH WEREN'T
PROVIDING SOAP TO CHILDREN AND
WOMEN IN DETENTION SO THEY COULD
PREVENT CONTAGIOUS DISEASES.
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
WOULD DIE IN THOSE CAMPS WHILE
PARLIAMENT ARGUED OVER WHETHER
IT WAS FAIR TO CALL THEM
CONCENTRATION CAMPS.
IN GERMANY, A MAN WAS ARRESTED
AND TAKEN WHERE NAZIS PUT A SIGN
AROUND HIM TO HUMILIATE HIM.
ARGUMENTS OVER WHAT TO CALL IT,
DEATH FROM CONTAGIOUS DISEASES.
WHAT WE HAVE IS NOT A DEATH CAMP
SYSTEM LIKE AUSCHWITZ BUT IT IS
A CONCENTRATION CAMP SYSTEM, A
MALEVOLENT SYSTEM THAT HAS DEEP
ROOTS IN A POLARIZED SOCIETY
THAT IS WILLING TO DO HARM TO
VULNERABLE PEOPLE.
IF THE AUTHORITIES DON'T
INTERVENE, WE KNOW WHAT'S GOING
TO THAT HAPPEN, WE'LL MOVE TO
THE NEXT STAGE OF CONCENTRATION
CAMP ABUSES, WHICH ARE GOING TO
SHOW UP NOT AS NEGLIGENCE BUT
ATROCITIES.
>> I'M GOING TO ASK YOU TO
PLEASE COME BACK.
>> CAN I ADD SOMETHING.
>> VERY QUICKLY.
>> SO, JOY, I THINK THE BIGGER
ISSUE, TOO, IS THAT WE KNOW THAT
A LOT OF THESE FOLKS THAT ARE
GETTING THESE GOVERNMENT
CONTRACTS ACTUALLY SERVED AS
SECURITY GUARDS FOR AFGHANISTAN
AND IRAQ.
THEY HAVE NO BUSINESS BEING
SURROUNDED BY CHILDREN.
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
I WANT TO HAVE YOU GUYS COME
BACK.
WE WANT TO THINK ABOUT WHAT
THESE CHILDREN CAN DO.
WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO
NEXT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, MARIA
THERESA KUMAR, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH ALL THREE.
>>> LATER THIS HOUR, WE'RE GOING
TO TALK ABOUT DISTURBING
INFORMATION, ABOUT THE CULTURE
AT THE BORDER PROTECTION AGENCY.
PLEASE STAY TUNED FOR THAT.
COMING UP NEXT, EVEN AFTER HE
WAS SLAPPED BY THE SUPREME
COURT, DONALD TRUMP IS NOT
GIVING UP ON HIS ATTEMPTS TO RIG
THE CENSUS.
JUST GETTING BETTER AND BETTER
AND BETTER.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
ETTER AND BR
AND BETTER
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
It would mean the world
to them,
and they will love you
forever.
>>> OFFICIALS IN SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA ARE ASSESSING THE
DAMAGE AFTER THE SECOND POWERFUL
EARTHQUAKE IN THE REGION IN JUST
THE LAST TWO DAYS.
FRIDAY'S QUAKE HAD A MAGNITUDE
OF 7.1 AND WAS CENTERED IN THE
DESERT CITY OF RIDGECREST, FELT
IN LOS ANGELES AND LAS VEGAS.
IT RATTLED HOMES AND BUSINESSES
AND SPARKED FIRE AND POWER
OUTAGES.
AT A BASEBALL GAME BETWEEN THE
LOS ANGELES DODGERS AND SAN
DIEGO PADRES, DODGERS STADIUM
SEEMED TO SHAKE AND ROLL FOR
NEARLY A MINUTE, BUT THE PLAYERS
PLAYED ON.
FRIDAY'S QUAKE COMES ONE DAY OF
A 6.4 MAGNITUDE EARTHQUAKE IN
THE SAME REGION.
OFFICIALS SAY THERE WILL LIKELY
BE MORE.
STAY WITH MSNBC THROUGHOUT THE
DAY FOR THE LATEST ON THIS
STORY.
UP NEXT ON A.M. JOY, TRUMP AND
HIS FAR RIGHT ALLIES WANT TO RIG
THE CENSUS BUT SINCE HE'S DONALD
TRUMP, HE MAY HAVE ALREADY
TANKED HIS OWN CASE.
VE ALREADY
With New Nicorette Coated
Ice Mint.
Layered with flavor...
It's the first and only coated
nicotine lozenge.
For an amazing taste...
...that outlasts your craving.
New Nicorette Ice Mint.
>>> THE CENSUS IS A
CONSTITUTIONALLY MANDATED
OPERATION THAT WE ARE REQUIRED
TO IMPLEMENT EVERY TEN YEARS.
IT IS ONE OF THE MOST VITAL AND
SENSITIVE THINGS THAT WE DO IN
OUR GOVERNMENT.
I WANT TO KNOW WHY THIS QUESTION
WAS MAGICALLY ADDED AFTER WE
HAVE SEEN THAT A POLITICAL
OPERATIVE KNEW AND DETAILED AN
INTENT TO INTIMIDATE RACIAL AND
IMMIGRANT COMMUNITIES FOR A
PARTISAN PURPOSE?
>> A RECENT SUPREME COURT
DECISION LAST MONTH IN WHICH
CHIEF JUSTICE JOHN ROBERTS SIDED
WITH THE LIBERALS ON THE COURT
MADE IT CLEAR THE MAJORITY ON
THE COURT SAW THROUGH THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S ATTEMPTS TO RIG
THE CONSTITUTIONALLY REQUIRED
UNITED STATES CENSUS TO TRY AND
TAKE MONEY AND RESOURCES AWAY
FROM NONWHITE PEOPLE AND
IMMIGRANTS.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION'S
ATTEMPTS TO PRETEND THAT THEY
REALLY WANTED TO ADD A
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION TO THE
CENSUS TO HELP THEM ENFORCE THE
VOTING RIGHTS ACT WERE EASILY
SEEN RIGHT THROUGH.
THE CAREER LAWYERS AT THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT SEEMED
CONTENT TO LISTEN TO THE COURT.
APPARENTLY DONALD TRUMP WAS NOT.
AFTER GOING ON A TWITTER TIRADE,
APPARENTLY AFTER CONOODLING WITH
HIS ALLIES, HE ORDERED THE DOJ
TO TRY AGAIN.
ON FRIDAY, TRUMP INVENTED A NEW
POWER THAT HE THINKS HE HAS AS
PRESIDENT SAYING HE'S
CONSIDERING AN EXECUTIVE ORDER
TO FORCE THE CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION ON TO CENSUS.
>> WE'RE THINKING ABOUT DOING
THAT.
IT'S ONE OF THE WAYS.
WE HAVE FOUR OR FIVE WAYS WE CAN
DO IT.
WE CAN ALSO ADD AN ADDITION ON.
WE CAN START THE PRINTING ON AND
MAYBE DO AN ADDENDUM AFTER WE
GET A POSITIVE DECISION SO WE'RE
WORKING ON A LOT OF THINGS,
INCLUDING AN EXECUTIVE ORDER.
>> IT SHOULD GO WITHOUT SAYING,
YOU CANNOT OVERRULE A SUPREME
COURT DECISION WITH AN EXECUTIVE
ORDER.
JOINING ME NOW IS MSNBC LEGAL
ANALYST, MAYA WILEY, ADAM
SERWER
OF THE ATLANTIC.
CAN ONE OVERRULE THE SUPREME
COURT DECISION BY HAVING AN
EXECUTIVE ORDER.
>> NO.
>> SO LET'S MOVE ON TO THE NEXT
QUESTION.
I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT.
BUT IT'S IMPORTANT TO MAKE IT
CLEAR.
>> I THINK WHAT'S REALLY
IMPORTANT HERE, IS JUSTICE
ROBERTS IN HIS OPINION SAID THAT
JUDICIAL REVIEW IS NOT JUST AN
EMPTY VEHICLE, THAT IT HAS TO
HAVE MEANING.
HE WAS EXPLICIT IN THE OPINION.
THINK ABOUT THIS, A CHIEF
JUSTICE OF THE SUPREME COURT
FELT THE NEED TO SAY THAT IN AN
OPINION.
THAT IS ASTOUNDING AND DONALD
TRUMP HAS PROVEN WHY IT WAS
NECESSARY TO SAY.
YOU KNOW, DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE
LAWYERS RIGHT NOW ARE TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO DO WHAT THEY
HAVE AN OATH TO DO, WHICH IS
UPHOLD THE LAWS OF THE UNITED
STATES AND THERE IS NO HIGHER
LEGAL VEHICLE IN THE LAND IN
TERMS OF HOW TO UNDERSTAND OUR
CONSTITUTION OR INTERPRET OUR
STAFF STATUTES THAN THE SUPREME
COURT.
>> THE STORY THAT'S DEVELOPING
IS DONALD TRUMP GETS SLAPPED
DOWN BY THE SUPREME COURT, THEN
WITH HIS FRIENDS ON THE FAR
RIGHT, THE ALT-RIGHT, FOLKS LIKE
STEPHEN BANNON, WHOEVER HE WAS
TALKING TO.
HE GETS MAD, DOES THIS TWEET
FORM, THAT IT'S FAKE, THEY'RE
NOT GOING TO FIGHT TO GET THE
QUESTION ON THE CENSUS, WHICH IS
JUST A STRAIGHT OUT LIE, AND NOW
YOU HAVE THE DEPARTMENT OF
JUSTICE TWISTING ITSELF INTO
KNOTS TO TRY TO FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO DO WHAT THEY HAVE BEEN TOLD
TO DO WHICH IS TO STILL FIND A
WAY TO GET THIS ISSUE ON TO THE
CENSUS.
WE KNOW FROM THE REPORTING
THAT'S OUT THERE IS THE ORIGINAL
REASON FOR IT IS THAT THEY
WANTED TO DEFUND AREAS THAT HAD
A LOT OF IMMIGRANTS IN IT,
ESPECIALLY NON-WHITE IMMIGRANTS.
THEY WANT TO GIVE WHITE VOTERS
AN ADVANTAGE, KNOWING
6.5 MILLION PEOPLE WOULDN'T
ANSWER THE CENSUS.
THE FACT THAT THEY'RE MAKING IT
THIS BLATANT, YOUR THOUGHTS.
>> I WANT TO SAY ONE THING, THIS
IS NOT A QUESTION OF FAR RIGHT.
THIS IS THE REPUBLICAN
ESTABLISHMENT THAT HATCHED THIS
SCHEME FOR WEAKENING THE VOTING
INFLUENCE OF VOTERS OF COLOR TO
INCREASE WHITE VOTING POWER.
THIS IS AN ABSOLUTELY
ESTABLISHMENT REPUBLICAN SCHEME
THAT DONALD TRUMP RECOGNIZES IS
IMPORTANT IF THE REPUBLICAN
PARTY WANTS TO KEEP WINNING
ELECTIONS IN A DIVERSIFYING
COUNTRY.
THEY NEED TO FIGURE OUT A WAY TO
MAKE WHITE VOTES COUNT MORE, AND
WHEN THEY WENT TO THE SUPREME
COURT, THEY GAVE THEM A
FICTIONAL REASON AND OF ALL THE
CONSERVATIVE JUSTICES ON THE
SUPREME COURT, ONLY ROBERTS WAS
WILLING TO SAY IT WAS FICTIONAL.
THE OTHER SUPREME COURT JUSTICES
SAID THAT THE PLAINTIFFS WERE
ASKING LIKE CONSPIRACY THEORISTS
IN SUGGESTING THE COMMERCE
SECRETARY WAS LYING.
NOW THE PRESIDENT HAS CONFIRMED
IT, THIS IS ABOUT DISTRICTING,
THIS IS ABOUT DILUTING THE
MINORITY VOTE.
THIS IS NOT ABOUT ENFORCING THE
MINORITY RIGHTS ACT.
EVERYONE KNEW THAT WAS A
PRETEXT, BUT WHAT THEY TRIED TO
DO WAS NOT SIMPLY LIE TO THE
COURT, NOT SIMPLY LIE TO THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE BUT TELL THEM
THE THING THAT THEY WERE SEEING
IN FRONT OF THEIR EYES WAS
FALSE.
>> YEAH, AND JUST TO SHOW YOU
ALL THAT, YOU KNOW -- AND THANK
YOU FOR MAKING THAT POINT
BECAUSE THIS HAS BEEN A
LONG-TERM THING TRYING TO GAME
AND GAME AND GAME THE SYSTEM
BECAUSE THEY KNOW DEMOGRAPHICS
ARE CHANGING AND THEY DON'T WANT
IT TO CHANGE THEIR POWER.
LET ME PLAY THE DONALD TRUMP
SOUND BITE, WHERE DONALD TRUMP
ADMITS IT'S ABOUT DISTRICTING,
USING THE CENSUS TO INCREASE THE
POWER OF HIS SIDE.
>> YOU NEED IT FOR MANY REASONS.
YOU NEED IT FOR CONGRESS, FOR
DISTRICTING.
YOU NEED IT FOR APPROPRIATION,
WHERE ARE THE FUNDS GOING, HOW
MANY PEOPLE ARE THERE, ARE THEY
CITIZENS, NOT CITIZENS, YOU NEED
IT FOR MANY REASONS.
>> MAYA NORMALLY WHEN SOMEBODY
IS BLATANT ABOUT THE WHOLE
REASON THEY'RE GOING IN FRONT OF
THE COURT IS A LIE, THAT WOULD
BE THE END OF IT, BUT DONALD
TRUMP HAS GOTTEN AWAY WITH IT
BEFORE.
HE SAID THE MUSLIM BAN WAS A
MUSLIM BAN AND HE SAID I DIDN'T
MEAN IT.
ROBERTS HAS NOT BEEN A HUGE FAN
OF VOTING RIGHTS.
COULD THEY JUST CHANGE THEIR
REASON AND SLIDE THIS RIGHT PAST
THE SUPREME COURT?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, HERE'S --
IT'S A LITTLE BIT COMPLICATED
BUT PROCEDURALLY, BUT LET'S SAY
THIS, ONE OF THE THINGS THAT
CHIEF JUSTICE ROBERTS DID WAS
SPENT ABOUT 22 PAGES SAYING WHY
THE ADMINISTRATION COULD PUT
THIS QUESTION ON THE CENSUS
DESPITE THE FACT THAT THE
CAREERISTS, THE PEOPLE WHO
BEHAVE IN A NONPARTISAN WAY IN
THE CENSUS BUREAU SAID NO, WE
DON'T THINK THIS QUESTION SHOULD
GO ON IN ORDER TO DO WHAT WE
NEED TO DO AS A CENSUS.
THAT'S REALLY IMPORTANT, AND
WHAT MINORITY ON THE COURT SAID,
WHAT LIBERALS ON THE COURT SAID
WAS WE ACTUALLY DON'T THINK THE
WHOLE FIRST PART OF THAT OPINION
IS RIGHT.
WE THINK THAT THIS WAS ARBITRARY
AND CAPRICIOUS, WHICH IS THE
LEGAL LANGUAGE FOR AIN'T NO
REASON FOR THIS, NO GOOD REASON,
THAT THE FACT THAT THE
CAREERISTS SAID NO, THIS IS BAD,
MEANS IT SHOULDN'T HAPPEN, AND
JUST ONE MORE THING I JUST WANT
TO ADD.
2010 REPUBLICANS UNDER FUNDED
THIS CENSUS EVEN BEFORE TRUMP
WAS ELECTED.
>> ABSOLUTELY, AND THEY SORT OF
MADE WAR ON IT.
LET ME GO TO YOU QUICKLY
NATASHA, HOW WILL THIS LOOK ON
THE GROUND, IF PEOPLE ARE AFRAID
TO ANSWER THE CENSUS, THEN WHAT?
>> I THINK PART OF THE PROBLEM
OF PEOPLE ARE AFRAID TO ANSWER
THE CENSUS, WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO
SEE IS A GROSS UNDERCOUNT.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE AN
UNDERCOUNT IN COMMUNITIES OF
COLOR, AND THE CHALLENGE IS THEY
ARE $800 MILLION OF AID THAT
GOES BY CENSUS DATA.
YOU'LL SEE A GROSS UNDERCOUNT
BECAUSE OF THIS.
I THINK THERE'S ANOTHER ISSUE I
WANT TO RAISE AROUND THE
PRESIDENT THAT WE HAVE A ROGUE
PRESIDENT THAT IN THIS PROCESS
IN PARTICULAR, HERE IS THE
EXECUTIVE THAT'S SAYING THAT
IMMEDIATELY AFTER THE SUPREME
COURT RULING, HE'S ACTUALLY
SAYING THAT I'M CONSIDERING
THESE OPTIONS.
ONE, I'M CONSIDERING THIS OPTION
AROUND EXECUTIVE ORDER, AND THEN
THE SECOND THING HE'S SAYING,
HE'S CONSIDERING THE OPTION OF
ADDING AN ADDENDUM.
THIS IS A PRESIDENT THAT DOES
NOT EVEN RESPECT THE LAW OF THE
LAND.
I REALLY THINK THAT WE'RE IN A
CONSTITUTIONAL CRISIS, AND WE
DON'T NEED TO ACT LIKE THIS IS
NORMAL.
THIS IS NOT NORMAL.
THIS IS NOT ACCEPTABLE.
THIS IS BEYOND.
HE TOOK AN OATH AND SWORE THAT
HE WOULD ACTUALLY UPHOLD THE LAW
OF THE LAND, YET WE'RE SEEING
THIS PLAY OUT VERY DIFFERENTLY.
I THINK WE NEED TO MAKE THE
DISTINCTION THAT HERE IT IS THAT
IMMEDIATELY AFTER THE SUPREME
COURT MADE A DECISION, HE SAYS
THAT HE'S GOING TO DO WHATEVER
HE WANTS TO DO ANYWAY AND WE'VE
GOT TO TAKE THAT SERIOUSLY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
HOPEFULLY THERE'S A PLAN.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE YOU TALK
ABOUT THIS MORE.
WE'LL HAVE YOU BACK TO TALK
ABOUT WHAT THE PLAN IS GOING TO
BE, IF HE'S SOMEHOW ABLE TO
THWART THE LAW.
THE SECRET FACEBOOK GROUP OF
BORDER PATROL AGENTS THAT IS
RAISING NEW QUESTIONS ABOUT THE
TREATMENT OF MIGRANTS AND THE
CULTURE OF THE CVP, THAT'S NEXT.
t
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
Fidelity is redefining value.
Introducing zero account fees
for brokerage accounts.
And zero minimums
to open an account.
At Fidelity,
those zeros really add up.
♪ Maybe I'll win,
saved by zero ♪
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
We're the Tenney's
and we're USAA members for life.
Call USAA to start saving
on insurance today.
Oh my, this Heinz mayonnaise
is so creamy,
and one day you'll tell yourife.
grandkids about it.
And they'll say, "grandpa just
tell us about humpty dumpty".
And you'll say, "he broke his
pelvis or whatever,
now back to my creamy
Heinz mayonnaise".
Heinz mayonnaise,
unforgettably creamy.
>>> 92% OF THE FORCE IS LATINO.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ASK ME HOW DO
THEY GET LATINO PEOPLE TO BEHAVE
THIS WAY AGAINST PEOPLE WHO ARE
THEIR OWN HERITAGE AND THEIR OWN
CULTURE.
IT'S BECAUSE IN THE ACADEMY THEY
MANDATE AND THEY TEACH THE
AGENTS TO USE RACIST TERMS FOR
MIGRANTS SO THAT THEY SEE THESE
PEOPLE AS OTHER AND THAT THEY
ARE NOT LIKE THEM.
IT DOES HAVE AN EFFECT.
IT'S CONDONED AND WHEN IT
HAPPENS AND SOMEBODY COMPLAINS,
EVERYBODY GROUPS TOGETHER,
SPECIFICALLY MORE THE MALE SIDE,
AND THEY PROTECT EACH OTHER.
>> A SECOND FORMERLY SECRET
FACEBOOK GROUP FREQUENTED BY
CURRENT AND FORMER CUSTOMS AND
BORDER PATROL AGENTS HAVE BEEN
UNEARTHED.
CNN OBTAINED SCREEN SHOTS FROM
TWO SOURCES FAMILIAR WITH THE
FACEBOOK PAGES THAT CONTAIN
BOLDER AND SEXUALLY EXPLICIT
POSTS MOCKING MIGRANTS AND
DEMEANING LAWMAKERS LIKE
ALEXANDRIA OCASIO CORTEZ.
NBC NEWS HAS NOT INDEPENDENTLY
IDENTIFIED THESE FACEBOOK GROUPS
OR POSTS.
BACK WITH ME, MIA WILEY AND
ADAM.
FEELING KINDA CUTE TODAY.
IDK.
YOU HAVE ANOTHER ONE THAT POSTED
THE FATHER AND DAUGHTER, ASKED
IF THE PHOTO COULD HAVE BEEN
FAKE BECAUSE THE BODIES WERE SO,
QUOTE, CLEAN.
IT GOES ON AND ON AND ON.
SOME ARE LATINO.
IT'S NOT ALL ONLY WHITE MEMBERS
OF THE CBP.
WHAT THE HECK IS GOING ON IN
YOUR VIEW?
>> ANY TIME YOU GIVE ONE GROUP
OF PEOPLE AUTHORITY OVER ANOTHER
GROUP OF PEOPLE YOU RUN THE RISK
THAT THE PEOPLE WITH AUTHORITY
ARE GOING TO SEE THEMSELVES AS
ABOVE OR BETTER THAN THE PEOPLE
WHO THEY HAVE AUTHORITY OVER.
THE WAY YOU MITIGATE THAT IN A
DEMOCRACY, YOU SAY THEY ARE
PUBLIC SERVANTS.
THEY ARE ACTUALLY EMPLOYED BY
THE PUBLIC, THEY DON'T LORD OVER
THE PUBLIC.
THE PROBLEM WITH THAT IS IF YOU
CREATE A CULTURE OF IMPUNITY
WHERE PUBLIC SERVANTS WHO HAVE
THAT AUTHORITY, PARTICULARLY
AUTHORITY OVER LIFE AND DEATH
ARE NEVER HELD ACCOUNTABLE WHEN
THEY ABUSE THAT AUTHORITY, THEN
THEY BEGIN TO RATIONALIZE THOSE
ABUSES AS SOMEHOW JUSTIFIED
ORNES.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT WE'RE SEEING
HERE, PARTICULARLY WITH THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IMPOSING
POLICIES THAT ARE CRUEL BEYOND
WHAT WE'VE SEEN IN PREVIOUS
ADMINISTRATIONS, EVEN WHEN THOSE
ADMINISTRATIONS HAVE BEEN STRICT
ON IMMIGRATION ENFORCEMENT.
AND THE PEOPLE WHO CARRY OUT
THOSE POLICIES HAVE TO BE ABLE
TO FIGURE OUT A WAY TO JUSTIFY
WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
AND ONE WAY THAT THEY DO THAT IS
BY DENYING THE HUMANITY OF THE
PEOPLE THAT THEY ARE -- THEY
HAVE AUTHORITY OVER.
>> YOU KNOW, THE DEHUMANIZATION
OF THESE FOLKS, IT DID REMIND
ME, CHRIS HAYES PUT UP A POST,
THESE AREN'T EVEN PEOPLE OR IN
OUR OWN PAST THE WAY THAT PEOPLE
WERE ABLE TO TREAT OTHERS,
WHETHER IT'S FROM ENSLAVEMENT
ON.
THEY'RE JUST NOT PEOPLE SO WE
DON'T HAVE TO THINK OF THEM AS
HUMAN BEINGS.
YOU HAVE THIS CUSTOMS AND
BOARDER PROTECTIONS PERSON
SAYING THIS DOES NOT REFLECT THE
VALUES OF CBP.
THEY'RE TWO DIFFERENT GROUPS
WHERE PEOPLE ARE MAKING
MOCKERIES.
MIA.
>> THEY'RE CLEARLY NOT TRUE.
WE HAVE NO REASON TO BELIEVE
THEY AREN'T BECAUSE THERE WAS A
2018 EXPOSURE.
THE FACEBOOK GROUPS EXISTED IN
2018.
I THINK PART OF THE PROBLEM HERE
IS EXACTLY WHAT ADAM SAID, THE
LEADERSHIP HAS TO SAY NOT ONLY
IS THIS NOT WHO WE ARE AS AN
INSTITUTION, IT IS NOT WHAT WE
WILL TOLERATE AS MANAGERS.
AND THAT'S CRITICALLY IMPORTANT.
IF YOU DON'T TAKE ACTION WHERE
YOU HAVE THE AUTHORITY TO TAKE
ACTION AGAINST EMPLOYEES, IN
THIS CASE THERE IS AN ABILITY TO
TAKE DISCIPLINARY ACTION IF
THERE'S INAPPROPRIATE SOCIAL
MEDIA ACTIVITY.
YOU HAVE TO BALANCE THAT WITH
FIRST AMENDMENT RIGHTS OF
COURSE, BUT HERE THE QUESTION IS
PEOPLE WHO HAVE THE ABILITY WHO
ARE ARMED WHO CAN ACTUALLY
VIOLATE THE HUMAN RIGHTS OF
OTHER PEOPLE MUST BE HELD TO
ACCOUNT WHEN THEY ARE
ESSENTIALLY DEHUMANIZING IN A
WAY THAT REALLY UNDERMINES THE
EFFECTIVENESS OF THE AGENCY,
WHICH IS SUPPOSED TO BE
IMPARTIAL.
REMEMBER THAT PEOPLE COMING TO
THE BORDER HAVE A LAWFUL RIGHT
BASED IN INTERNATIONAL LAW AS
WELL AS U.S. LAW TO SEEK ASYLUM
AND THE DEHUMANIZATION IS BOTH
OFFENSIVE BUT IT ALSO
FUNDAMENTALLY UNDERMINES THE
ROLE THAT THEY ARE TO PLAY AT
THE BORDER AND WE SHOULD BE VERY
CONCERNED ABOUT THAT.
>> BUT, I MEAN, TO -- I THINK I
TOLD YOU EVERY WEEK, ADAM,
CRUELTY IS THE POINT.
THAT'S WHY THEY'RE DOING IT.
HIS BASE WANTS TO SEE THIS SO
HE'S SHOWING THEM THAT HE CAN
DEHUMANIZE THEM.
ISN'T THAT MESSAGE COMING FROM
THE WHITE HOUSE THAT ESSENTIALLY
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TREAT THESE
PEOPLE LIKE HUMAN BEINGS.
WHO CARES?
>> I DO THINK THE MESSAGE IS
COMING FROM THE WHITE HOUSE THAT
THESE PEOPLE ARE NOT HUMAN
BEINGS AND YOU DON'T HAVE TO
TREAT THEM PROPERLY.
I WILL SAY THOUGH THAT WHEN IT
COMES TO CHILDREN THE
ADMINISTRATION IS VERY AWARE
THAT ITS POLICIES ARE AT THEIR
POLITICAL WEAKEST POINT WHEN
PEOPLE SEE THESE IMAGES OF
CHILDREN BEING ABUSED OR BEING
HELD IN DEHUMANIZING CONDITIONS.
WITH THE ADULTS IT'S A LITTLE
DIFFERENT.
THE PRESIDENT LIKES TO BRAG
ABOUT HOW HE'S GOING TO DEPORT A
MILLION PEOPLE, THEY'RE GOING TO
DO A CRACKDOWN AND ALL OF THAT
STUFF.
WHEN IT COMES TO THE CHILDREN, I
ACTUALLY THINK THAT THEY
RECOGNIZE THAT THIS IS DAMAGING
FOR THEM AMONG EVERYONE AMONG
THE MOST HARD CORE TRUMP
SUPPORTERS.
>> THEY DON'T DO ANYTHING ABOUT
IT, MAYA.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN THEY'RE
CHANGING IT.
THEY WON'T LET THE KIDS GO.
THEY WON'T LET THEM GO.
THEY'RE HOLDING THEM FOR ALMOST
60 DAYS AT SOME POINT.
THEY JUST WON'T LET THEM GO.
>> THEY WON'T LET THEM GO.
>> IF THEY SEE THAT IT'S WRONG,
WHY WON'T THEY LET THEM GO?
>> THEY WON'T LET THEM GO.
THEY HAVE THE ASTOUNDING
APPEARANCE IN COURT WHERE THEY
WERE IN VIOLATION OF THE
SETTLEMENT AGREEMENT.
OH, WELL, WE DON'T EVEN HAVE TO
PROVIDE SOAP.
>> YEAH.
THEY MOVED THEM TO ANOTHER
FACILITY BECAUSE THEY KNEW THAT
THE CAMERAS WERE COMING.
MOCKED THE MEMBERS OF CONGRESS
IN FRONT OF THE SUPERVISORS WHO
DID NOTHING AND THEN MOVED THE
KIDS RIGHT BACK IN.
IF THEY REALLY BELIEVED THAT, IF
THEY SAID THEY WERE GOING TO
DEPORT THEM, THEY'RE NOT DOING
THAT.
IT'S INSANE.
MAYA, WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
ADAM SEWER, REALLY APPRECIATE
YOU.
KEEP ON QUOTING YOU.
MORE "AM JOY" AFTER THE BREAK.
B.
With TripAdvisor,
it's easy to discover over
100,000 bookable things to do,
from walking tours in Rome
to wine tastings in Tuscany,
and if you like what you see,
you can book it with ease.
Just another way TripAdvisor
helps you make your trip
a masterpiece.
♪ Hoo
- Read reviews, check hotel
prices, book things to do.
TripAdvisor.
Do you want me to go first or
do you want to go first, Brea?
You can go first.
Audible reintroduced this
whole world to me.
So many great stories
from amazing people.
It makes me want
to be better.
To be able to connect with
the people's stories
that I'm listening to.
That's inspiration.
It's on during my commute,
it's on all the time.
Doing the dishes.
Working out.
While I'm in the car.
At bed time.
An Audible listener
is someone that
wants to broaden
their mind.
People who are
tired of listening
to the radio, or music.
To hear her speak
those words.
It was incredible.
It was unbelievable.
With Audible Originals,
there's something for almost
every taste in there.
Everything you ever
wanted to hear.
I signed up for getting
a credit every month,
and I started exploring books
that I normally wouldn't read.
Our ability to empathize
through these stories,
with these stories,
can be transformational.
It's my own thing that
I can do for me.
See what listening to
Audible can do for you.
Just text Listen14
to 500500.
>>> I KNOW PREDATORS, AND WE
HAVE A PREDATOR LIVING IN THE
WHITE HOUSE.
AND THE THING ABOUT PREDATORS
YOU SHOULD KNOW IS THAT THEY
PREY ON THE VULNERABLE.
THEY PREY ON THOSE WHO THEY DO
NOT BELIEVE ARE STRONG.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "AM JOY."
ALMOST THREE YEARS AFTER HILLARY
CLINTON BECAME THE FIRST MAJOR
NOMINEE OF A U.S. POLITICAL
PARTY, WE NOW HAVE SIX WOMEN
RUNNING.
AMONG THEM, SENATOR KAMALA
HARRIS.
WHO AMONG CALLING DONALD TRUMP A
PREDATOR SHARES WHY SHE HAS THE
CREDIBILITY TO TAKE HIM DOWN.
>> I'VE HAD A LOT OF FIGHTS,
MOST OF WHICH I'VE WON.
I KNOW HOW TO FIGHT.
LET ME TELL YOU, WE'RE GOING TO
NEED SOMEBODY WHO CAN
SUCCESSFULLY PROSECUTE THE CASE
AGAINST ANOTHER FOUR YEARS OF
THAT ADMINISTRATION.
I KNOW HOW TO DO THAT.
>> SENATOR HARRIS ALONG WITH
SENATOR ELIZABETH WARREN SAW
THEIR STOPS SOAR IN NEW NATIONAL
POLLS.
THE QUINNIPIAC POLL THAT WAS
RELEASED TUESDAY SHOWS HARRIS
SURGING 13 POINTS SINCE LAST
MONTH INTO SECOND PLACE.
ONLY TWO POINTS BEHIND
FRONT-RUNNER JOE BIDEN.
THAT AFTER HARRIS CHALLENGED
BIDEN OVER HIS COMMENTS ABOUT
WORKING WITH SEGREGATIONIST
SENATORS AND HIS OPPOSITION TO
FEDERALLY MANDATED BUSSING IN
THE 1970s.
WHEN ASKED WHICH CANDIDATE DID
THE BEST JOB AT THE DEBATE, 47%
SAID HARRIS.
SHE WAS FOLLOWED BY SENATOR
ELIZABETH RAR WEN WITH 17%.
6% SAID BIDEN HAD THE BEST
PERFORMANCE.
WHEN ASKED WHICH CANDIDATE HAS
THE BEST POLICY IDEAS WARREN
TOOK THE LEAD WITH 31% COMPARED
TO 19% IN APRIL.
SANDERS CAME IN AT 18% WHILE
BIDEN RECEIVED 11%, A DROP FROM
23 IN APRIL.
DESPITE THESE NUMBERS, BIDEN
REMAINS THE NOMINAL FRONT-RUNNER
EVEN IF BARELY.
THE CHANGES IN THE STANDINGS ARE
RE-UPPING THE QUESTION WHETHER
AMERICA IS FINALLY, FINALLY
READY TO ELECT A WOMAN
PRESIDENT.
THERE ARE SIX OPTIONS.
IF NOT NOW, WHEN?
MAYA WILEY IS WITH ME.
JOINING ME IS RASHAD ROBINSON,
TIFFANY CROSS AND DEAN OBIDALA.
I'M GOING TO YOU FIRST, RASHAD
WATCHING MISSY ELLIOT AT THE
ESSENCE FESTIVAL.
I'M WONDERING IF YOU HAD A
CHANCE.
I DON'T KNOW WHEN YOU GOT HERE.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HAD A CHANCE
TO WALK AROUND WITH PEOPLE THAT
YOU ARE RUNNING AROUND DOWN HERE
AT ESSENCE.
TELL ME WHAT YOU'RE HEARING.
IS THE KAMALA BOOM RESONATING IN
THE REAL WORLD OR IS IT US
PEOPLE OBSESSED WITH POLLS?
>> I THINK IT'S A MIX OF BOTH.
IT IS PEOPLE THAT ARE OBSESSED
WITH POLLS AND THOSE OF US IN
THE POLITICAL CLASS THAT FOLLOW
THESE THINGS ARE SORT OF DEEPLY
INVESTED IN LOOKING AT THE UP
TICKS AND DOWN TICKS BUT PEOPLE
ARE UNDERSTANDING WHO SHE IS,
PAYING CLOSER ATTENTION TO US
AND THAT'S THE POWER OF THE
DEBATES.
I'M ALSO HEARING ELIZABETH
WARREN'S NAME A LOT FROM A
NUMBER OF PEOPLE AS I WALK
AROUND, PARTICULARLY THE WAY
SHE'S ROLLED OUT A SET OF PLANS
AND EXACTLY HOW SHE'S TALKING
ABOUT HOW SHE'S GOING TO CLOSE
SOME OF THE GAPS THAT HAVE
PLAGUED COMMUNITIES FOR SO LONG.
I DO THINK IT'S INCREDIBLY
EARLY.
EVEN THE TICKS AND HITS THAT
BIDEN HAS TAKEN TO HIS POLLS IS
A RECOGNITION THAT MANY OF HIS
EARLY NUMBERS WERE JUST THAT
PEOPLE KNEW WHO HE WAS.
IT'S LIKE GOING INTO A STORE, A
SUPERMARKET AND YOU PICK THE
PRODUCT OFF THE SHELF THAT YOU
HAVE SEEN THE MOST COMMERCIALS
FOR, THAT YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE THE
MOST ATTENTION TO.
OVER TIME YOU MIGHT CHANGE THAT
AS YOU LEARN MORE THINGS.
SO I DO THINK THAT IT'S JUST
REALLY EARLY BUT I DO THINK THAT
THESE DEBATES ARE SHIFTING THE
LANDSCAPE AND GIVING PEOPLE MORE
OPPORTUNITY TO SEE CANDIDATES IN
A DIFFERENT WAY.
>> THAT'S A VERY GOOD POINT,
TIFFANY.
THERE IS A CERTAIN HUGE
ADVANTAGE THAT BIDEN HAD BECAUSE
PEOPLE KNEW WHO HE IS.
PEOPLE DIDN'T KNOW WHO A LOT OF
THESE PEOPLE WERE.
PEOPLE WATCHED THE SECOND
DEBATE, OH, SHE'S INTERESTING.
I'M WONDERING IF THERE'S A
POTENTIAL THAT IT'S A LITTLE
DEEPER AND PEOPLE DIDN'T KNOW
WHO BARACK OBAMA WAS BUT WHEN
THEY SAW HIM IN COMPARISON AND
SAW HE WAS PLAUSIBLE.
BIDEN IS ONLY TWO POINTS AHEAD
IN THE LATEST POLL.
WARREN IS RIGHT UP THERE.
SHE'S PASSED BERNIE SANDERS, AT
14.
STATISTICALLY TIED BUT ONE POINT
AHEAD OF HIM.
SHE'S UP 13, HARRIS.
BIDEN'S GONE DOWN 8.
SHE'S TAKING THAT LEAD FROM HIM
IT LOOKS LIKE.
I WONDER IF HE'S A BIT TOO
COMFORTABLE ASSUMING I'M THE GUY
BLACK VOTERS LIKE.
AMONG AFRICAN-AMERICANS, SHE'S
ONLY FOUR POINTS DOWN AMONG
AFRICAN-AMERICANS.
THAT'S A HUGE CHANGE.
IT FEELS A LITTLE BIT LIKE
BARACK OBAMA VERSUS HILLARY
CLINTON IN THAT '08 PRIMARY OR
AM I READING TOO MUCH INTO IT?
>> FIRST I HAVE SERIOUS FOMO
THAT ALL OF YOU GUYS ARE AT THE
ESSENCE FESTIVAL.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ABOUT MISSY
ELLIOTT.
BUT BACK TO THE ISSUE AT HAND,
BACK TO THE POINT.
I THINK A LOT OF -- SO MANY
PEOPLE PUT HOW THEY FEEL ABOUT
THESE CANDIDATES THROUGH THE
LENS OF CABLE NEWS NETWORKS,
RIGHT?
SO WHEN YOU HAVE PEOPLE OFFERING
ANALYSIS IN HOW THEY FEEL EVEN
AFTER THE DEBATE, A LOT OF TIMES
THAT CONVERSATION IS DRIVEN BY A
MEDIA LACKING IN DIVERSITY,
ETHNIC DIVERSITY, DIVERSITY IN
THOUGHT, SOCIOECONOMIC
DIVERSITY.
PEOPLE LOOK THROUGH A MYOPIC
LENS.
IT BECAME ALL ABOUT ELIZABETH
WARREN, KAMAL HAD A HARRIS.
WE FORGET THAT JULIO CASTRO HAD
AN AMAZING PERFORMANCE.
VERY OVERLOOKED CANDIDATE.
I THINK WE HAVE TO LOOK AT THIS
AND TO THAT POINT IT IS STILL
VERY EARLY IN THE PROCESS.
YOU AND I TALK ABOUT THIS A LOT,
JOY.
YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL ABOUT THE
POLLS.
POLLS ARE MOSTLY OLDER
AMERICANS, PEOPLE WHO ANSWER
LAND LINES.
PEOPLE WHO ANSWER LAND LINES
FROM AN UNIDENTIFIED CALLER,
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE A LOT
OF PEOPLE DOING THAT.
WE HAVE TO DISAGGREGATE THE
DATA.
I THINK KAMALA HARRIS IS A VERY
ELECTABLE CANDIDATE.
THERE ARE OTHERS WHO ARE
ELECTABLE.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE WILL
ULTIMATELY SAY, YEAH, ULTIMATELY
YOU CAN'T PUT ALL YOUR CREDENCE
INTO WHAT POLLS ARE SAYING AND
MEDIA ANALYSTS EVEN SAY.
SO WE HAVE TO -- THERE'S ANOTHER
DEBATE COMING UP A THE -- AT THE
END OF JULY.
WE HAVE TO LOOK AT IT AT A WIDER
MAINSTREAM OUTLET.
>> YOU KNOW, I AGREE WITH YOU.
WE TALK ABOUT THIS ALL THE TIME.
I HAVE TO SAY, I'M GOING TO DEAN
ON THIS, HERE'S THE CHALLENGE.
EVERYTHING TIFFANY JUST SAID IS
TRUE BUT MOST PEOPLE DON'T HAVE
TIME TO FOLLOW THIS.
THEY LOOK AT THE POLLS, LISTEN
TO US TALK ABOUT IT.
YOU TALK ABOUT THE GREAT DEBATE
THAT JULIAN CASTRO HAD.
HE DIDN'T MOVE IN THE POLLS.
IT FEEDS ON IT SELF.
HE HAD A GREAT DEBATE BUT HE
DIDN'T MOVE.
THE THING IS PEOPLE ARE TRYING
TO THINK.
I HAVE TO NAIR COULD HE 800
PEOPLE DOWN TO FOUR, RIGHT?
THEY HAVE TO START THINKING OF
IT AS FOUR OR FIVE INSTEAD OF
40.
THE NEXT DEBATE DO YOU THINK THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY OUGHT TO NARROW
IT DOWN A LITTLE BIT?
IT WOULD ELIMINATE SOMEONE WHO'S
NOT POLLING VERY MUCH?
DO YOU THINK IT'S BAD TO DO
ANOTHER 23 PEOPLE IN THE DEBATE?
>> THE JULY DEBATE, LET IT GO
FORWARD.
THE NEXT DEBATE, SEPTEMBER,
ALREADY THE FIELD IS SMALLER.
LOOK, THIS IS GOING TO BE A
BATTLE.
I MEAN, DONALD TRUMP TALKED
ABOUT IT ON THE FOURTH OF JULY
LIKE WHEN THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
TOOK UP AIRPORTS.
IT'S THAT KIND OF BATTLE WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT, THE BATTLE OF
LAGUARDIA, ONWARD TO JFK.
THIS IS THE KIND OF BATTLE
THAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN BETWEEN
NOW AND NOVEMBER OF 2020.
INTERNALLY IN THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY, THINGS ARE GOING TO
CHANGE.
PEOPLE WANT SOMEONE TO WIN.
THERE ARE THREE FACTORS THEY
WANT IN THE DEMOCRATIC NOMINEE,
WHO CAN BEAT TRUMP, WHO CAN BEAT
TRUMP, WHO CAN BEAT TRUMP.
THEY SAY EVERY TIME, VOTE BLUE
NO MATTER WHO.
WHOEVER I'M SUPPORTING IS FINE.
WE'RE GOING TO UNITE AND WIN
AGAINST DONALD TRUMP.
THE MORE POLLS YOU SEE WHERE
SENATOR HARRIS CAN BEAT TRUMP.
THE MORE WHERE SENATOR WARREN
CAN BEAT TRUMP.
NOT JUST BIDEN CAN BEAT TRUMP IT
MAKES THEM MORE ELECTABLE AND I
THINK UNDERCUTS THE IDEA THAT
JOE BIDEN IS THE ONLY ONE
ELECTABLE AND THE MORE THAT
HAPPENS, I THINK THE MORE JOE
BIDEN CAN STILL BE THE NOMINEE
BUT POTENTIALLY SLIDES.
>> YEAH.
PUTTING ASIDE THE FACT THAT DEAN
BROUGHT UP THE BATTLE IN WHICH
GEORGE WASHINGTON, YOU KNOW,
USED HIS FIGHTER PLANES TO BOMB
THE BRITISH FRONT LINE, YOU
KNOW, DURING THAT FIRST BATTLE
TO TAKE OVER THE AIRPORTS DURING
THE REVOLUTIONARY WAR.
WE'RE GOING TO PUT THAT ASIDE
AND COME BACK TO POLITICS, MAYA
WILEY.
THE OTHER ISSUE, AS DEAN SAID,
IT'S BEEN SEEN BIDEN IS THE ONLY
ONE WHO CAN BEAT TRUMP.
THERE HAS BEEN THIS IDEA EVEN
AMONG AFRICAN-AMERICANS, IT'S
GOT TO BE A WHITE GUY.
WHEN YOU SEE HER BEAT HIM IN A
DEBATE, DOESN'T THAT MAKE PEOPLE
WONDER, WAIT A MINUTE, HE CAN'T
BEAT HER, MAYBE THIS WOMAN
ACTUALLY IS THE ONE WHO CAN TAKE
DONALD TRUMP DOWN?
>> YEAH, I THINK THAT'S RIGHT.
I THINK ONE OF THE THINGS THAT'S
HAPPENING HERE IS THE SORT OF
NATIONAL TRAUMA AROUND DONALD
TRUMP HAVING WON THE 2016
ELECTION.
REMEMBER THAT HILLARY CLINTON
DID WIN BY ALMOST 3 MILLION
VOTES, WHAT SHE LOST WAS THE
ELECTORAL COLLEGE.
SHE LOST THAT BY BASICALLY THREE
STATES IN THE MIDWEST, RIGHT?
IT WAS PENNSYLVANIA, WISCONSIN
AND MICHIGAN.
SO THAT'S WHERE THE OH, WE NEED
A WHITE MAN FEAR COMES FROM BUT
I ALSO THINK THE FACT THAT
VOTERS VOTED FOR DONALD TRUMP
DESPITE HIS OVERT SEXISM IS PART
OF WHY WE ARE STARTING TO HEAR
WHAT I THINK IS A VERY DANGEROUS
DEBATE ABOUT WHETHER IS A WOMAN
ELECTABLE.
WHAT WE DON'T TALK ABOUT IS IS A
BLACK WOMAN ELECTABLE?
PART OF WHAT'S HAPPENING IS THIS
NOTION IS THE ONLY WAY WE WIN
THE OFFICE IS BY ACTUALLY
SACRIFICING WHO WE ARE WHEN ALL
OF THE FUNDAMENTALS SHOW THAT
ABSOLUTELY WOMEN AND WOMEN OF
ALL RACES ARE ELECTABLE.
THAT'S WHAT 2018 TAUGHT US.
IN FACT, BACK TO YOUR EARLIER
POINT, JOY, ABOUT BARACK OBAMA,
ONCE HE WON THE IOWA CAUCUSES,
HE WAS WAY BEHIND HILLARY
CLINTON IN THE POLLS, WAY
BEHIND.
WHEN HE BEAT HER BY, WHAT, ABOUT
8 POINTS IN THE IOWA CAUCUS IN
'08, SUDDENLY HE WAS ELECTABLE.
IT IS EARLY.
I AGREE WITH EVERYTHING EVERYONE
ELSE SAID.
I THINK WE HAVE TO ADDRESS THE
FACT THAT OUR FEAR COULD BE OUR
WORST ENEMY IN TERMS OF GETTING
THE KIND OF LEADER WE NEED FOR
THE COUNTRY.
>> CAN I TOP IN, JOY?
>> YEAH.
>> REALLY QUICKLY TO MAYA'S
POINT.
I THINK SOME PEOPLE VOTED FOR
DONALD TRUMP DESPITE THESE
THINGS.
WE HAVE TO RECONCILE SOME PEOPLE
VOTED FOR DONALD TRUMP BECAUSE
OF THESE THINGS.
WE SEE UGLY RHETORIC.
THESE GUYS ARE NOT RUNNING
AGAINST DONALD TRUMP, THEY'RE
RUNNING AGAINST EACH OTHER.
WE HAVE TO GET THROUGH A
PRIMARY.
I TAKE DEAN'S POINT OBVIOUSLY
KAMALA HARRIS IS ELECTABLE.
IT IS SOMETHING VOTERS SHOULD
PAY ATTENTION TO.
SHE HANDLED JOE BIDEN.
I THINK THERE IS AN UNDERBELLY
OF PEOPLE WHO ARE DYING TO SEE
HER BODY DONALD TRUMP ON A
DEBATE STAGE, DYING TO SEE HER
SLAP HIM AROUND ON THE DEBATE
STAGE WHICH SHE COULD HANDLE
WELL BUT WHO'S DOING THE ASKING?
WHO'S SAYING IS A BLACK WOMAN
ELECTABLE?
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE PEOPLE WHO
ARE QUESTIONING THAT, THEY
FREQUENTLY DON'T LOOK LIKE SOME
OF US ON THE PANEL.
SOMETIMES THEY DO.
SOMETIMES THERE ARE PEOPLE OUT
OF SOUTH CAROLINA WHO REALLY DO
THINK THAT BLACK PEOPLE CAN BE,
YOU KNOW -- WE CAN QUESTION
OURSELVES IN A WAY THAT
SOMETIMES NOT EVEN, YOU KNOW,
WHITE PEOPLE QUESTION.
>> YEAH, I MEAN --
>> TO THAT POINT --
>> GO ON.
GO ON.
>> TO TIFFANY'S POINT, WHICH I
THINK IS EXCELLENT, THAT'S WHY
THIS HAS TO BE ABOUT EXPANDING
THE BASE.
EXPANDING ELECTORATE, NOT ABOUT
HOW MANY TRUMP VOTERS CAN BE
PEELED OFF BUT WHERE ARE THE '08
AND 2012 OBAMA VOTERS?
THAT MEANS THIS CONVERSATION
THAT OFTENTIMES THE POLITICAL
CLASS TALKS ABOUT WITH LOW
PROPENSITY VOTERS BUT WE LIKE TO
TALK ABOUT HIGH POTENTIAL
VOTERS.
THE BLACK VOTES, THE PEOPLE OF
COLOR, THE YOUNG PEOPLE WHO
OFTENTIMES NEVER GET TALKED TO.
WHO IS GOING TO INSPIRE THOSE
VOTERS TO TURN OUT?
BECAUSE ACTUALLY WE CAN EXPAND
THE BASE OF VOTERS AND TURN OUT
PEOPLE THAT HAVE OTHERWISE NOT
TURNED OUT IN THE LAST ELECTION
AND DON'T TURN OUT OFTENTIMES IN
ELECTIONS, WE NOT ONLY WIN
ELECTIONS BUT WE WIN WITH THE
TYPE OF BASE THAT ALLOWS US TO
GOVERN IN PROGRESSIVE WAYS.
TO PASS THE TYPE OF LEGISLATION
AND THE TYPE OF POLICY AND
PRACTICE CHANGE THAT THESE ARE
TALKING ABOUT.
SO TO THE POINT OF BOTH THE
CONVERSATION ABOUT WHO IS HAVING
THIS CONVERSATION IN THE MEDIA
AND HOW THE MEDIA IS COVERING
THIS BUT ALSO WHO THESE
CANDIDATES ARE TALKING TO, THIS
HAS TO BE A STORY ABOUT NOT JUST
APPEALING TO THE LOWEST COMMON
DENOMINATOR BUT APPEALING TO THE
ASPIRATIONS AND EXPANDING THE
BASE OF VOTERS.
THAT'S WHY NEW VOICES AND VOICES
THAT ARE UNAFRAID, WOMEN, PEOPLE
OF COLOR ARE GOING TO BE SO
IMPORTANT TO USHERING THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY INTO THE NEXT
PHASE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
DEMOCRATIC PARTY HAS TO DECIDE.
DO THEY HAVE TO DO A SORT OF --
KIND OF A NOSTALGIA VERSION OF
THEMSELVES NORTH TO MOLLIFY A
CERTAIN VOTER OR GO FORWARD.
THE WOMEN SEEM TO BE LEADING
THAT CONVERSATION AT THE MOMENT.
MAYA WILEY, RASHAD ROBINSON,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
TIFFANY AND DEAN WILL BE RIGHT
BACK.
>>> COMING UP, WE'RE GOING TO
TALK BIDEN AND WHETHER THIS PAST
WEEK WAS A GLITCH OR WAS IT THE
FIRST HOLE THAT THE ICEBERG
RIPPED INTO THE SIDE OF THE
TITANIC?
THAT'S NEXT.
Alice loves the smell
of Gain so much,
she wished it came in
a fabric softener too.
[throat clears]
Say hello to your fairy
godmother, Alice.
Oh and look they got Gain scent
beads and dryer sheets too!
(VO)
Parents have a way of imagining
the worst...
...especially when your easily
distracted teenager has the car.
At Subaru, we're taking on
distracted driving
[PING]
with sensors that alert you when
your eyes are off the road.
The all-new Subaru Forester.
The safest Forester ever.
>>> I WAS PREPARED FOR THEM
COMING AT ME.
I WASN'T PREPARED FOR THE PERSON
SHE KNOWS BO, SHE KNOWS ME.
>> IT WAS THE MOST DRAMATIC
BREAKOUT MOMENT OF THE
DEMOCRATIC DEBATE.
SENATOR KAMALA HARRIS
CONFRONTING FORMER VICE
PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN FOR BOASTING
ABOUT WORKING WITH NOTORIOUSLY
RACIST SEGREGATIONIST SENATORS
IN PAST DECADES AND HIS STANCE
ON BUSSING.
ON FRIDAY BIDEN DID AN INTERVIEW
ON CNN TRYING TO CLEAN UP.
>> I THINK IF YOU TAKE A LOOK
OUR POSITIONS AREN'T ANY
DIFFERENT AS WE'RE FINDING OUT.
>> YOU WERE NOT IN FAVOR OF
BUSSING.
IT WAS A DIFFERENT TIME AND
DIFFERENT APPLICATIONS, WHY NOT
OWN IT.
WHY NOT SAY, I WAS AGAINST IT
AND NOW I'VE CHANGED.
>> I WAS IN FAVOR OF BUSSING.
THE QUESTION IS HOW DO YOU
EQUALIZE EDUCATION IN EVERY
AREA?
I PUT FORWARD THE MOST
AGGRESSIVE PLAN AND I'VE BEEN
PUSHING IT FOR A LONG TIME.
>> TIFFANY CROSS AND DEAN ARE
BACK WITH ME.
JOINING ME IS WILL BUNCH OF THE
PHILADELPHIA INQUIRER.
PHIL, I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT THIS.
BIDEN HAS NOW BEEN COMPARED TO
JEB BUSH.
GAIL COLLINS SAID SHE WORRIED
BIDEN WOULD BE THE JEB BUSH.
SHE SAID FEEBLE.
HE'S THE GUY WHO CAN BEAT TRUMP.
ANOTHER PERFORMANCE LIKE THIS
ONE AND HE'S DONE.
MORE IMPORTANTLY WHAT YOU'RE
SEEING FROM BIDEN IS THAT HE
DOES SEEM TO BE A CANDIDATE
GEARED TOWARDS THE PAST.
I'M GOING TO BRING BACK A PAST
THAT YOU LIKED WHICH IS THE
OBAMA ERA.
HE DOESN'T FEEL LIKE A CANDIDATE
OF THE FUTURE.
IS THAT A PROBLEM IN THIS RACE?
>> I THINK SO.
ABSOLUTELY.
I WAS AT HIS ANNOUNCEMENT IN
PHILADELPHIA AND I THOUGHT
PEOPLE WERE PARTYING LIKE IT WAS
2015.
HE WANTS TO GO BACK TO THE NEAR
PAST, RIGHT?
TO THE OBAMA YEARS.
I THINK EVERYTHING THAT'S
HAPPENED IN THE LAST THREE OR
FOUR YEARS I THINK PEOPLE ARE
LOOKING FOR A NEW DIRECTION
FORWARD.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE TO SAY IN THAT
SOUND BITE YOU PLAYED WHERE HE
SAID HE WASN'T EXPECTING THE
KAMALA HARRIS MOMENT, THAT'S
REALLY SURPRISING TO ME.
HE'S REALLY HAD 40 YEARS TO
PREPARE FOR IT.
HE COULD TELL A GOOD STORY ABOUT
HIS EVOLUTION ON CIVIL RIGHTS UP
TO THE POINT WHERE HE BECAME THE
VICE PRESIDENT TO THE FIRST
BLACK PRESIDENT IN THIS COUNTRY
AND HE REALLY FUMBLED THE ANSWER
TO WHERE HE WAS MUMBLING
SOMETHING ABOUT STATES RIGHTS.
IT REMINDED ME OF THE LAUNCH OF
RONALD REGAN'S 1980 CAMPAIGN IN
MISSISSIPPI.
I THINK THE BROADER PROBLEM IS
JOE BIDEN HAS BEEN ON THE
DEFENSIVE SINCE THE DAY HE
ENTERED THIS RACE AND I THINK
DEMOCRATIC VOTERS ARE REALLY
LOOKING FOR AFFIRMATIVE REASONS
TO SUPPORT A CANDIDATE.
I MEAN, I THINK THAT'S WHY
YOU'VE SEEN ELIZABETH WARREN
RISE SO MUCH IN THE POLLS,
BECAUSE SHE'S PUT OUT PLAN AFTER
PLAN AND BECOME A HASHTAG
#IHAVEAPLANFORTHAT.
BIDEN HASN'T CAPTURED THE PUBLIC
IMAGINATION.
I KNOW HE HAS SOME.
LAST NIGHT THERE WAS A NEW VIDEO
OF HIM MAKING THE ROUNDS WHERE A
VOTER IN IOWA CONFRONTED HIM
ABOUT WHAT HE WAS GOING TO
ABOUT BRETT KAVANAUGH AND THE
SUPREME COURT.
HE TOLD HER HE DIDN'T HAVE AN
ANSWER FOR THAT.
A LOT OF CANDIDATES DON'T HAVE
AN ANSWER FOR THAT.
I THINK AGAIN AND AGAIN IF YOU
ARE GOING TO SEE JOE BIDEN
TRYING TO DEFEND HIS PAST RECORD
OR TRYING TO JUSTIFY HIS
CANDIDACY BEYOND JUST HE THINKS
HE CAN BEAT DONALD TRUMP, YOU'RE
GOING TO SEE HIM CONTINUE TO
ERODE IN THE POLLS IF THAT'S HIS
STYLE AND THAT'S THE WAY HE
CAMPAIGNS.
>> YEAH, TIFFANY, THERE'S
SOMETHING ABOUT EVEN THAT, THE
THING THAT WILL JUST MENTIONED,
ABOUT HIM SAYING HE'D NOMINATE
MAYOR GARLAND AND SAY HE'S GOING
TO GO GET THAT GUY.
EVEN WHEN PRESIDENT OBAMA
NOMINATED HIM, PEOPLE SHRUGGED
UNTIL MITCH McCONNELL SAID NO TO
HIM.
THE REALITY IS, DEMOCRATS LOVE
JOE BIDEN.
DEMOCRATS LOVE UNCLE JOE, BUT IS
THAT ENOUGH OF A REASON TO
NOMINATE HIM TO BE PRESIDENT?
DOES HE NEED A FORWARD-LOOKING
STRATEGY THAT ISN'T JUST YOU
LOVE ME, I'M UNCLE JOE?
>> RIGHT.
IF VOTERS ARE CONCERNED, WE WANT
TO VOTE FOR THE PERSON WHO CAN
BEAT DONALD TRUMP, IF JOE BIDEN
WAS NOT PREPARED FOR THIS MOMENT
ON BUSSING, WHAT WILL HE NOT BE
PREPARED FOR WHEN HE'S ON THE
DEBATE STAGE WITH DONALD TRUMP?
THIS IS A LEGITIMATE QUESTION
THAT PEOPLE HAVE TO ASK
THEMSELVES.
AND, LISTEN, IT IS NOT ENOUGH IN
TODAY'S SOCIETY IN A POST TRUMP
AMERICA FOR YOU TO SAY, NO, NO,
NO, BUT WAIT, MY BEST FRIEND WAS
BLACK.
I SERVED THE FIRST BLACK
PRESIDENT.
LET ME GO THROUGH THIS CLUMSY
EXPLANATION ON HOW I CAME TO
SOME OF THESE POLICY POSITIONS.
THAT IS NOT GOING TO RESONATE
WITH VOTERS, PARTICULARLY WE SAW
IN THE MID TERMS THE SURGE IN
YOUNGER VOTERS WHO WERE YOUNGER
PEOPLE DURING THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION WHO ARE PAYING
MORE ATTENTION IN THIS
LEGISLATIVE ENVIRONMENT.
I THINK HE HAS A LOT OF WORK TO
DO TO RESONATE WITH VOTERS.
YOU HAVE TO ALSO LOOK LIKE WE
KNOW SOME OF THE PEOPLE WHO WORK
ON JOE BIDEN'S STAFF.
IT'S LIKE NOBODY, DID YOU NOT
ALL THINK THAT QUESTION WOULD
COME UP?
AND WHY THIS TOPIC IS EVEN BEING
DISCUSSED IN THE FIRST PLACE IS
BECAUSE HE STARTED OUT BY
SAYING, LISTEN, GUYS, I CAN WORK
WITH SEGREGATIONISTS.
I CAN WORK WITH WHITE
SUPREMACISTS BECAUSE I HAVE DONE
IT BEFORE.
I DON'T THINK A LOT OF PEOPLE
ARE LOOKING FOR YOU TO WORK WITH
THESE PEOPLE.
PEOPLE ARE LOOKING FOR YOU TO
GET THESE PEOPLE OUT ROOT AND
STEM AND REDEFINE WHAT THIS
GOVERNMENT SHOULD BE AND COULD
BE FOR ALL PEOPLE INCLUDING
PEOPLE OF COLOR WHO HAVE BEEN
DISENFRANCHISED FOR DECADES.
>> YEAH.
LET ME TELL YOU WHAT BIDEN SAID.
THIS IS AN -- DEAN, I WANT TO
PLAY THIS FOR YOU.
THIS IS JOE BIDEN TALKING ON CNN
WHEN HE DID THIS INTERVIEW WITH
CHRIS COMEAU.
>> I THINK IT WOULD BE GREAT TO
HAVE A FEMALE VP.
IF I DON'T WIN I THINK IT WOULD
BE GREAT TO HAVE A FEMALE
PRESIDENT.
>> DO YOU THINK THE DEMOCRATIC
TICKET CAN WIN WITHOUT A WOMAN
IN THE SLOTS?
>> YES.
BUT I THINK IT HELPS TO HAVE A
WOMAN ON THE TICKET.
THERE ARE A LOT OF REALLY
QUALIFIED WOMEN OUT THERE.
>> THAT MAKES THE POINT A LITTLE
BIT BECAUSE IT DOES TALK ABOUT
HIM SAYING, YEAH, IT WOULD BE
GREAT TO HAVE A FEMALE VP.
GREAT TO HAVE A WOMAN VP
EVENTUALLY.
THIS IS CUT ONE FROM MY
PRODUCERS.
THIS IS HIM SPEAKING ABOUT HOW
HE FELT BEING CONFRONTED BY
KAMALA HARRIS.
THIS IS CUT ONE.
>> IT WAS HURTFUL TO HEAR YOU
TALK ABOUT THE REPUTATIONS OF
TWO UNITED STATES SENATORS WHO
BUILT THEIR REPUTATIONS AND
CAREER ON THE SEGREGATION OF
RACE IN THIS COUNTRY.
AND IT WAS NOT ONLY THAT BUT YOU
ALSO WORKED WITH THEM TO OPPOSE
BUSSING.
>> SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I DIDN'T HAVE THE CUT THAT I WAS
LOOKING FOR.
THE ONE I WANTED TO PLAY FOR
YOU, I'LL JUST DESCRIBE IT TO
YOU, DEAN.
>> SURE.
>> HE SAYS TO CHRIS CUOMO THAT
IT WAS HURTFUL TO HIM TO BE
CONFRONTED THAT WAY BY KAMALA
HARRIS.
SHE KNOWS MY SON.
SHE KNOWS MY FAMILY.
SOMETHING ABOUT THAT I THINK HAS
A PERSON OF COLOR MAYBE HEARING
IT, IT FEELS LIKE HE FEELS LIKE
HE'S DONE SO MUCH.
I DON'T KNOW, IT FELT AS IF HE
FELT THAT HE SHOULDN'T BE
QUESTIONED IN A SENSE BECAUSE
HE'S BEEN BARACK OBAMA'S VP,
THAT HE SHOULDN'T BE QUESTIONED.
>> WELL, ON SOME LEVEL TO ME,
THAT COULD BE PART OF IT, IT
HARKENS BACK TO WHAT WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
JOE BIDEN IS A THROW BACK TO A
DIFFERENT TIME.
IN POLITICS THEY WOULDN'T ATTACK
YOU.
THEY'RE MY FRIEND.
TO REMIND PEOPLE IN 2016 IN THE
CALIFORNIA PRIMARY, PRESIDENT
OBAMA AND JOE BIDEN SUPPORTED
KAMALA HARRIS IN THAT PRIMARY.
HE CAMPAIGNED FOR HER.
HE KNOWS HER SON AS WELL.
HE WAS STUNNED.
SOMEONE WHO'S MY FRIEND ON THE
STAGE IN FRONT OF EVERYONE WOULD
MOCK ME.
THAT GOES BACK CRITICIZING ON
POLICY.
THAT GOES BACK TO AN OLDER VIEW
OF POLITICS.
HEY, WE'RE ALL FRIENDS.
WE'RE ONLY SLIGHTLY DIFFERENT ON
POLICY AND WE CAN ALL GET ALONG.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO WORK ANYMORE
TODAY IN 2020.
JOE BIDEN REMINDS US WHY IN 2008
HE GOT LESS THAN 1% OF THE VOTE
IN IOWA BEFORE HE DROPPED OUT OF
THE RACE.
HE WAS NOT A GREAT CANDIDATE.
I THINK HE MIGHT KNOW THE
POLICIES INSIDE AND OUT.
AS A CANDIDATE HE'S NOT PROVING
EACH OTHER.
HE'S GOING TO INSPIRE PEOPLE TO
GO AND KNOCK ON DOORS, DRIVE
THEIR FRIENDS TO POLLS, TO MAKE
PHONE CALLS AND DONATE MONEY.
HE'S GOING TO PICK UP HIS GAME
TO BE THAT PERSON.
IT'S JUST NOT GOING TO WORK.
I WAS THE VICE PRESIDENT.
I'M INEVITABLE.
GIVE ME THIS POSITION.
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN IN 2020.
I CAN ASSURE YOU HE STILL CAN BE
THE NOMINEE BUT IT'S NOT
INEVITABLE.
>> WELL, VERY QUICKLY.
LAST WORD TO YOU ON THIS.
DOES -- IS BIDEN RUNNING TOO
MUCH ON SAYING ESSENTIALLY THAT
HE'S -- HE WANTS TO BE
PRESIDENT -- DOES HE NEED TO
MAKE A CLEARER REASON WHY HE
WANTS TO BE PRESIDENT OTHER THAN
WHAT HE'S DONE IN THE PAST?
BECAUSE IT DOES FEEL LIKE HIS
CANDIDACY IS ROOTED IN A THING
LIKE I'VE DONE ALL OF THIS FOR
YOU IN THE PAST, NOW IT'S TIME
FOR ME TO BE PRESIDENT.
IT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE A
STRONG -- I DON'T KNOW, WHAT DO
YOU THINK?
>> YOU'RE ASKING ME?
>> I'M SORRY --
>> FOR WILL.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S OKAY.
PEOPLE WANT TO KNOW WHAT HE'S
GOING TO DO.
ALSO AT HIS ANNOUNCEMENT HE
SAYS, YOU KNOW, YOU WANT TO DO
SOMETHING ABOUT CLIMATE CHANGE,
BEAT DONALD TRUMP.
THAT'S HOW YOU DO SOMETHING
ABOUT CLIMATE CHANGE.
ON SOME LEVEL THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU HAVE OTHER CANDIDATES WITH
MUCH MORE DETAILED PLANS.
WHEN HE TALKS ABOUT MERIT
GARLAND, THAT'S A PERFECT
REMINDER WHY THE CONGENIAL
APPROACH FROM THE 1970s THAT HE
WANTS TO BRING BACK ISN'T GOING
TO WORK IN THE 21st CENTURY.
HOW CAN SOMEBODY WHO WAS THERE
FOR MERRITT GARLAND AND WHAT
MITCH McCONNELL DID TO HIM THINK
HE CAN GET ALONG WITH
REPUBLICANS IN ANY WAY?
THEY HAD A POLICY OF EIGHT YEARS
OF TRYING NOT TO GET ANYTHING
FOR OBAMA, TO DENY HIM A SECOND
TERM AND TO DENY HIM A SUPREME
COURT SEAT.
AND WHY THAT WAS SUDDENLY
CHANGED WITH THE INSTALLATION OF
JOE BIDEN AS PRESIDENT, I JUST
DON'T SEE THAT AT ALL.
>> YEAH, I'M NOT SURE THAT YOU
CAN BEAT MASSIVE RESISTANCE WITH
COMMITY.
DEAN AND TIFFANY WILL BE BACK.
WILL BUNCH, WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
WE'LL HAVE YOU BACK ON AGAIN.
>>> COMING UP.
AFTER MULTIPLE INDOOINLTS, OVER
10,000 LIES AND BOWING TO
DICTATORS ACROSS THE GLOBE
DONALD TRUMP HAS SEEN EXACTLY
ONE ELECTED REPUBLICAN QUIT
THEIR PARTY.
JUSTIN AMISH'S INDEPENDENCE DAY
NEXT.
NEXT
and skills and effort
and talent.
Please consider volunteering
and feeling that feeling that
you helped someone today.
♪♪
-
Play it cool and escape
heartburn fast
with new TUMS Chewy
Bites Cooling Sensation.
♪ TUM TUM TUM TUMS ♪
>>> OKAY.
A QUICK NOTE OF HOST PRIVILEGE.
I WANT TO THANK EVERYONE WHO HAS
BOUGHT MY BRAND-NEW BOOK "THE
MAN WHO SOLD AMERICA, TRUMP AND
THE UNRAVELING OF THE AMERICAN
STORY."
THIS WEEK IT BECAME A "NEW YORK
TIMES" BEST SELLER.
SUPER BUCKET LIST EXCITING.
THANKS TO ALL OF THE FOLKS WE
MET AT THE ESSENCE FEST.
YOU CAN GET YOUR COPY WHEREVER
BOOKS ARE SOLD.
COMING UP, MORE "AM JOY."
-Driverless cars...
-All ground personnel...
...or trips to Mars.
$4.95.
Delivery drones
or the latest phones.
$4.95.
No matter what you trade,
at Fidelity
it's just $4.95 per online
U.S. equity trade.
>>> I WAS HOPING TO SET AN
EXAMPLE FOR PEOPLE.
I'VE BEEN INVOLVED IN PARTY
POLITICS FOR A WHILE AND I
BELIEVE VERY STRONGLY THAT IT'S
HURTING OUR COUNTRY AT THIS
POINT.
AND I THINK PEOPLE NEED TO STAND
UP FOR WHAT'S RIGHT, STAND UP
FOR WHAT THEY BELIEVE IN AND BE
INDEPENDENT OF THESE PARTY
LOYALTIES THAT REALLY DIVIDE US.
>> THAT IS FORMER AND THAT IS
RIGHT FORMER REPUBLICAN
CONGRESSMAN JUSTIN AMASH WHY HE
CHOSE TO LEAVE THE PARTY
CHOOSING, YOU GUESSED IT, THE
FOURTH OF JULY TO HAVE HIS
INDEPENDENCE.
HE EXPLAINED HIS DECISION TO
QUIT THE PARTY ENTIRELY IN A
"WASHINGTON POST" OP ED SAYING
TRUE TO WASHINGTON'S FEARS, THEY
HAVE IGNORED THE MOST BASIC
TENANTS OF OUR CONSTITUTIONAL
ORDER.
THE RESULT HAS BEEN THE
CONSOLIDATION OF POLITICAL POWER
AND THE NEAR DISINTEGRATION OF
REPRESENTATIVE DEMOCRACY.
BACK WITH ME IS DEAN AND NOELLE
AND JASON JOHNSON, NOT THE
JOURNALIST JASON JOHNSON.
CONSULTANT AND FORMER ADVISOR OF
TED CRUZ.
THERE ARE TWO OF YOU GUYS.
YOU KNOW THIS GUY.
TELL US A LITTLE BIT ABOUT HIM.
HE IS AN INTERESTING CHARACTER.
>> A LOT OF MUTUAL FRIENDS.
WHAT I DO ADMIRE A GREAT DEAL,
IT TOOK THE SON OF A PALESTINIAN
REFUGEE TO STAND UP FOR
IMPEACHMENT.
I SAY THAT AS A SON OF A
PALESTINIAN IMMIGRANT.
LET'S BE CLEAR ABOUT ONE THING,
DONALD TRUMP CALLED HIM A
DISLOYAL REPUBLICAN.
THIS IS A GUY WHO IS A FOUNDER
OF THE FREEDOM CAUCUS.
THIS IS A GUY WITH A HIGHER
RATING FROM THE AMERICAN
CONSERVATIVE RATING, HIGHER THAN
LINDSEY GRAHAM.
IT'S NOT ABOUT LOYALTY TO
REPUBLICAN PARTY OR CONSERVATIVE
PRINCIPLES, IT'S LOYALTY TO
DONALD J. TRUMP.
HE REFUSED TO BE LOYAL TO HIM.
HE PUT THE CONSTITUTION ABOVE
HIS PARTY AND NOW HE'S PUT HIS
PARTY TO THE SIDE.
I STAND UP FOR THE UNITED STATES
OF AMERICA.
I APPLAUD HIM FOR THAT.
>> VERY QUICKLY, HE'S SYRIAN AND
PALESTINIAN?
>> HE'S 100% -- I'M A HALF ARAB
GUY.
HE'S A PURE OUT THERE.
I THINK IT'S PROBABLY SHOCKED A
LOT OF REPUBLICANS.
>> AND, NICK, IT USED TO BE --
I'M OLD ENOUGH TO REMEMBER WHEN
A PLURALITY, WE'RE GEARED
TOWARDS THE REPUBLICAN PARTY.
THERE'S BEEN A HUGE EXIT OF THE
PARTY BY PEOPLE IN THE
BACKGROUND.
HE'S NOT FOR THAT REASON.
HIS PIECE IN THE WASHINGTON POST
I THOUGHT WAS BRILLIANT.
HE REALLY EXPLAINED WHERE WE ARE
IN TERMS OF HYPER PARTISANSHIP
ERODING OUR POLITICS.
THAT'S REALLY ON ONE SIDE MORE
THAN THE OTHER.
YOU HAD THE REPUBLICAN PARTY SAY
BARACK OBAMA DOESN'T EXIST.
WE WILL MAKE HIM NOT EXIST.
WHY IS HE THE ONLY ONE, NOELLE?
>> I THINK IT WAS A WRONG MOVE
THAT HE LEFT THE REPUBLICAN
PARTY.
ALTHOUGH HE DOESN'T LIKE
PRESIDENT DONALD TRUMP, HE DOES
RESPECT THE PLATFORM OF THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY.
SO, YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY -- IN
MY OPINION, YOU REALLY CAN'T
MAKE CHANGE AND YOU REALLY CAN'T
MAKE A DIFFERENCE IF YOU JUST
QUIT, YOU JUST QUIT THE PARTY
BECAUSE YOU DON'T LIKE WHO'S
REPRESENTING THE PARTY.
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE GOT AN
OPPORTUNITY WHILE YOU'RE IN THE
PARTY TO GET OTHER PEOPLE TO
CONVINCE THEM, YOU KNOW, MAKING
CHANGE WITH POLICY.
REALLY THE WAY YOU MAKE CHANGE
IS IN POLICY, NOT BY QUITTING,
BECAUSE I KNOW HE'S NOT GOING TO
GO ON THE OTHER SIDE AND JOIN
THE DEMOCRAT PARTY.
SO IT JUST LEAVES HIM TO BE AN
INDEPENDENT AND THE LIKELIHOOD
OF HIM GETTING RE-ELECTED IS
PROBABLY NOT GOOD.
SO, THEREFORE, YOU KNOW, I WISH
THAT HE WOULD HAVE STAYED AND
MADE HIS CASE AND REALLY FOUGHT
FOR WHAT HE BELIEVED IN AND
TRIED TO CHANGE THE DIRECTION OF
THE CORE VERSUS JUST QUITTING
IT.
>> FIRST OF ALL, DEMOCRATIC
PARTY.
WE DON'T USE SORT OF FAKE NAMES.
WE'RE GOING WITH DEMOCRATIC
PARTY.
I WANT TO GO TO YOU, JASON.
LET'S SAY HE LOVES THE TAX CUTS
FOR THE RICH.
HE LIKES THAT REPUBLICAN THING.
I DON'T KNOW HOW HE COULD LIKE
THE KIDS IN CAGES.
LET'S SAY HE LIKES THAT, TOO.
WHAT HE SPECIFICALLY HAS A
PROBLEM WITH IS BREAKING THE
LAW.
THIS GUY HAS BEEN VERY CLEAR.
HE ACTUALLY READ THE MUELLER
REPORT.
HE'S ONE OF THE FEW IN CONGRESS
THAT READ IT.
HE SAID, OH, THIS GUY VIOLATED
TEN TIMES THE LAW THAT FEFGS A
CIVILIAN HE'D BE IN PRISON FOR
OBSTRUCTING JUSTICE.
IF YOU CAN'T BE FOR THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
HAVING TO ACTUALLY UPHOLD THE
LAW HE SWEARS TO UPHOLD, I'M NOT
SURE WHAT YOUR PURPOSE IS AS A
POLITICIAN.
DOESN'T HE GET CREDIT FOR SAYING
THIS GUY VIOLATED, I'M OUT OF
HERE.
>> JOY, TWO THINGS.
NUMBER ONE, I'M NOT GOING TO SIT
HERE AND TRY TO ARGUE THAT
JUSTIN AMASH'S EXIT FROM THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY AND DECLARING
HIMSELF INDEPENDENT IS DETACHED
AND HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH HIS
CALLING FOR IMPEACHMENT OF THE
PRESIDENT.
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT AND I
UNDERSTAND IT'S TEMPTING TO GET
WRAPPED UP IN JUST THE DONALD
TRUMP SECTION.
IF YOU READ THAT EDITORIAL, I,
TOO, THINK IT'S BRILLIANT.
THE REALITY IS LONG BEFORE
DONALD TRUMP CAME ON THIS HYPER
PARTISAN SHIP.
WHY SHOULD JUSTIN AMASH, A
MEMBER TODAY ELECTED BY HIS
DISTRICT OF THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES, BE ANY LESS
EFFECTIVE IN ARGUING FOR HIS
BRAND OF CONSTITUTIONAL
CONSERVATISM SIMPLY BECAUSE HE
DOESN'T HAVE AN "R" NEXT TO HIS
NAME?
I'M NOT SAYING HE WILL BE LESS
EFFECTIVE, THAT MAKES THE POINT.
THE PROBLEM THAT WE HAVE TODAY,
YOU EITHER ARE ON TEAM RED OR
TEAM BLUE AND I THINK WE ALL
KNOW THAT UNFORTUNATELY WE
LISTEN OR WE'RE OPEN MINDED TO
THE ARGUMENTS PRESENTED BASED
UPON THE COLOR OF THE OTHER
PERSON'S JERSEY, AND THAT'S
UNFORTUNATE.
IT SHOULDN'T BE THAT WAY.
>> TO THAT POINT, NOELLE, ANSWER
THAT.
IT'S TRUE.
IF YOU THINK HE IS WITH THE
CONSERVATIVE PRINCIPLES, IF HE
TAKES OFF OF TEAM RED PEOPLE
WON'T LISTEN TO HIM?
WHY SHOULDN'T HE HE GET
RE-ELECTED?
>> I FEEL LIKE THAT WE HAVE
TURNED POLITICS INTO A BLOOD
SPORT.
I MEAN --
>> BUT AREN'T YOU DOING THAT BY
SAYING THAT IF HE TAKES OFF THE
RED JERSEY, SUDDENLY HE CAN'T
GET RE-ELECTED.
WHY SHOULDN'T HE?
>> BECAUSE IT'S GOING TO BE HARD
TO RAISE MONEY, THAT'S NUMBER
ONE.
IF YOU HAVE TURNED YOUR BACK ON
THE GOP -- HE SAID HE WAS
QUITTING THE GOP.
HE COULD HAVE SAID, I'M QUITTING
TEAM TRUMP.
HE'S QUITTING THE GOP.
>> HOLD ON A SECOND.
DONALD TRUMP IS THE GOP.
DONALD TRUMP IS THE HEAD OF THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY.
HE'S RUNNING -- ALL OF THE
POLICIES THAT DONALD TRUMP IS
PUTTING IN PLACE, YOUR PARTY
100% IS STANDING BEHIND HIM ON
WHETHER IT'S THE CHILDREN IN
CAGES WHICH VIOLATES ALL KINDS
OF LAWS AND MAYBE THE GENEVA
CONVENTION.
THEY'RE BEHIND HIM ON TARIFFS
WHICH ARE DESTROYING PEOPLE'S
FARMS AND RANCHES, DESTROYING
THEIR LIVES.
THEY'RE BEHIND HIM ON EVERYTHING
HE DOES EVEN IF HE'S SAYING I'M
GOING TO IGNORE THE SUPREME
COURT.
IF NO ONE IS QUIT OVER THAT,
CHARLOTTESVILLE, NOTHING ELSE,
DOES THE GUY GET CREDIT FOR
SAYING HE HAS SOME PRINCIPLE?
AT SOME POINT HE SAYS ENOUGH.
>> HE TOTALLY GETS CREDIT FOR
BEING HIS OWN MAN AND STANDING
UP FOR THINGS THAT HE DOESN'T
BELIEVE IN OR AGREE WITH, BUT TO
QUIT THE PARTY.
THE PARTY IS NOT THE -- THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY PLATFORM IS NOT
DONALD TRUMP.
IT'S A PLATFORM --
>> BUT IT IS.
YES, IT IS.
IT IS DONALD TRUMP.
IT IS 100% DONALD TRUMP.
IT'S WHATEVER HE WANTS, HE DOES
IT.
WHATEVER DONALD TRUMP WANTS,
THAT'S THE PLATFORM.
>> BUT HE RAN UNDER THE GOP
LABEL.
THE GOP DIDN'T RUN ON HIS LABEL
OR HIS BRAND.
SO IN EFFECT --
>> SO THEN THE KIDS IN CAGES ARE
THE REPUBLICAN PLATFORM?
>> WELL, I -- I JUST FEEL LIKE,
YOU KNOW, BACK TO THE ORIGINAL
POINT, I JUST FEEL LIKE FOR HIM
TO TRY TO DO A RE-ELECTION
CAMPAIGN RAISING MONEY, TRYING
TO DEPEND ON MAJOR GOP DONORS TO
HELP GET HIS MESSAGE OUT.
I JUT DON'T SEE HIM GETTING
RE-ELECTED WHEN HE QUITS THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY.
I GUESS YOU'RE GOING TO RUN AS
AN INDEPENDENT.
>> YOU COULD.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING TO GET
THE FUNDING SOURCES FOR THAT?
>> IT'S ALL ABOUT MONEY.
LET ME GIVE JASON THE LAST
RECORD.
JASON, WILL THERE BE OTHER
JUSTIN AMASHs IN YOUR OPINION?
>> WE WILL SEE MORE MEMBERS.
IT'S AMAZING, OUT OF 435 ELECTED
REPRESENTATIVES IN THE PEOPLE'S
HOUSE, THERE NOW IS ONLY ONE
INDEPENDENT.
WE HEAR ALL THE TIME ABOUT HOW
AT LEAST 1/3 OF THE COUNTRY IS
IN FACT INDEPENDENT YET THERE'S
ONE OUT OF 435.
GO FORWARD, AND THIS APPLIES TO
BOTH PARTIES.
UNLESS THESE ARE COALITIONS OF
POLICY DEMANDERS START TO
RESPOND IN THEIR BASES, ON THE
BRAND I THINK WE WILL SEE MORE
INDIVIDUALS DECLARING THARP
INDEPENDENCE GO FORWARD.
>> LAST QUESTION FOR YOU, DEAN?
>> THEY MIGHT.
HE GOT A STANDING OVATION.
LET'S BE HONEST.
THE GOP IS ABOUT LOYALTY TO
DONALD TRUMP ONLY.
IT STANDS FOR NOTHING.
THE GOP IS TRUMP AND TRUMP IS
THE GOP.
IT'S A PARTY OF NOT TEAM RED,
IT'S TEAM TRUMP.
NOT ONE REPUBLICAN STOOD UP FOR
JUSTIN WHEN TRUMP SAID HE'S
DISLOYAL.
THE DICTATOR IN CHIEF DEMANDED
HE BE GONE.
>> I RECOMMEND EVERYONE READS
JUSTIN AMASH'S PIECE.
IT'S VERY GOOD.
>>> COMING UP, THE FREAK OUT
OVER A TEENAGE MERMAID AND WHAT
IT TELLS US ABOUT AMERICA'S
CULTURE WARS NEXT.
With tough food, your dentures
may slip and fall.
Fixodent Ultra-Max Hold
gives you the strongest hold
ever
to lock your dentures.
So now you can eat tough food
without worry.
Fixodent and forget it.
♪ Hoo
- I like to plan my
activities before I take trip,
so by the time I get there
I can just enjoy the ride.
With TripAdvisor,
it's easy to discover over
100,000 bookable things to do,
from walking tours in Rome
to wine tastings in Tuscany,
and if you like what you see,
you can book it with ease.
Just another way TripAdvisor
helps you make your trip
a masterpiece.
♪ Hoo
- Read reviews, check hotel
prices, book things to do.
TripAdvisor.
I have one kid in each branch
of the military,
but I'm command central.
It's so important to us
that Verizon
is supporting military families.
When I have a child deployed,
having a reliable network
means everything.
So, when I get a video chat,
and I get to see their face,
it's the best thing
in the world.
And I've earned every one
of these gray hairs.
Military moms, we serve too.
(VO)
The network more people rely on,
gives you more.
Like military plans with
a special price on Unlimited,
$100 per line, and big savings
on our best phones
when you switch.
That's Verizon.
♪ LIKE THE SONG OF LOVE THAT
CLINGS TO ME ♪
♪ HOW THE THOUGHT OF YOU DOES
THINGS TO ME ♪
♪ WISH THAT I AM UNFORGETTABLE
TOO ♪♪
>> VOICE OF DISNEY'S NEWEST
AERIAL, HALLIE BAILEY WHO IS SET
TO STAR IN THE LIVE ACTION
LITTLE MERMAID REMAKE.
WELL, NOW HERE'S WHAT YOU MAY
WANT TO HAVE ANY KIDS UNDER 12
LEAVE THE ROOM.
GIVE YOU A MOMENT, TAKE THEM OUT
THE ROOM.
OKAY.
SO MERMAIDS AREN'T REAL.
I KNOW, THEY'RE NOT REAL.
SO IN THEORY, ANYONE COULD PLAY
A MERMAID, RIGHT?
WRONG.
THE ANNOUNCEMENT OF HER CASTING
HAS CAUSED A MULTIDAY FREAKOUT
AMONG SOME DISNEY FANS WHO ARE
UPSIT THAT THE ACTRESS CAST TO
PLAY AERIAL IS NOT WHITE.
BACK WITH ME IS TIFFANY CROSS OF
THE BEAT D.C. AND JOINING ME
ENTERTAINMENT JOURNALIST CHRIS
WITHERSPOON.
THIS YOUNG LADY IS ADORABLE, THE
YOUNG LADY WHO'S GOING TO A
ARIEL.
>> YES.
SHE TWEETS OUT DREAM COME TRUE,
PEOPLE ARE EXCITED THAT YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE THIS LITTLE
AFRICAN AMERICAN GIRL BEING
ARIEL.
BUT THE FREAKOUT WAS REAL.
I THINK IT TRENDED FOR A COUPLE
DAYS AFTER THIS HAPPENED.
PEOPLE WERE SCREAMING SHE'S
SUPPOSED TO BE WHITE WITH RED
HAIR, WHAT THE "H"?
WHAT IS GOING ON?
>> I WAS SHOCKED BY THE FREAKOUT
MYSELF AND A LOT OF THE FOLKS
WHO ARE FREAKING OUT WERE WHITE
ADULTS WITH LITTLE MERMAID THAT
CAME ON THAT HAD THIS WHITE
DEPICTION OF A PRINCESS THAT WE
HAVE SEEN FOR DECADES.
I THINK THAT THE FREAKOUT IS
UNWARRANTED.
THE REREALITY IS THERE HAVE BEEN
11 DISNEY PRINCESSES.
GUESS HOW MANY OF THEM HAVE BEEN
BLACK.
JUST ONE.
SO 91% OF THE DEPICTION IN THE
NARRATIVE OF WHAT IT IS TO BE A
PRINCESS HAS BEEN THROUGH THIS
WHITE LENS.
IT'S PAST DUE.
AND THE LAST TIME WE HAD A BLACK
PRINCESS WAS TEN YEARS AGO.
SO CALM DOWN, HAVE SEVERAL
SEATS, AND LET'S EMBRACE HALLIE
AND ALL HEF TALENT.
SHE'S FIERCE AND SHE DESERVES
THIS ROLE HANDS DOWN.
>> LET ME READ ONE TWEET.
THANK YOU TO MY TEAM FOR PURTING
THIS UP THERE.
THIS SORT OF MADE THE POINT WELL
IN THE IS STEPHANIE RENEE WHO
SAYS MY CHILDREN WERE RAISED
WITH ARIEL.
SHE'S AN ICON IN THE EYES OF
MANUFACTURE CHILDREN AND ADULTS
OF TODAY.
SO CHANGE HER RACE IS ABSURD.
THAT WOULD BE LIKE SOMEBODY
MAKING A MOVIE OF OPRAH WINFREY
AND HIRING A WHITE GIRL TO PLAY
OPRAH.
FIRST OF ALL, SHE'S A REAL
PERSON.
SO IF YOU MADE A MOVIE ABOUT HER
YOU WOULD WANT TO HER TO LOOK
KIND OF LIKE OPRAH.
THIS ISN'T A DOCUMENTARY.
THERE'S NO SUCH PERSON AS ARIEL.
>> THERE'S NO TIME UNDER THE SEA
WHERE SEBASTIAN SAYS ARIEL AND
YOUR WHITENESS IN YOUR CAUCASIAN
EXPERIENCE, IT DOESN'T HAPPEN.
SO WE COULD EASILY RECREATE AND
RETELL THIS STORY HOWEVER WE SEE
FIT.
I THINK DISNEY IS DOING A GREAT
JOB AT BEING INCLUSIVE AND NEW
WAYS TO TELL DIVERSE NARRATIVES
AND COLORBLIND CASTING.
>> TIFFANY, WHEN MALCOLM "X" WAS
MADE, I THOUGHT THE MOVIE WAS
BRILLIANT.
I HAD A SLIGHT PROBLEM WITH
DENZEL WASHINGTON IS A GENIUS
BECAUSE HE'S DARKER SKIN AND
HAVING LIGHT SKIN WAS PART OF
MALCOLM "X'S" CHARACTER.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING AT SOMEONE
LIKE THAT, MAYBE THE CASTING WAS
ODD BECAUSE HIS WHOLE
PERSONALITY HAD TO DO WITH HIS
COMPLEXION.
BUT THIS ISN'T A DOCUMENTARY.
IT'S ABOUT A FICTIONAL PRETEND
CREATURE THAT'S A FISH.
>> AND EVEN THE CRAZY LADY
THAT'S TWEETING OUT THE TWEET
YOU JUST READ, HOW MANY WHITE
PEOPLE HAVE ACTUALLY PLAYED REAL
BLACK PEOPLE?
YOU'VE HAD WHITE ACTORS PLAY
MICHAEL JACKSON AND OTHER
PEOPLE.
HOW OFTEN DO YOUR STORIES GET
WHITEWASHED IN MAINSTREAM
HOLLYWOOD?
HONESTLY, I HAVE A THEY'RE PRIT
THINK THE NOT MY ARIEL THING
TRENDED BRIEFLY BECAUSE OF THOSE
FRINGE INTERNET SECTION COMMENTS
CRAZY PEOPLE WHO TWEET OUT THESE
RIDICULOUS THINGS.
BUT I THINK THE OVERWHELMING
MAJORITY OF PEOPLE WHO MADE THIS
TREND WERE PEOPLE WHO DISAGREED,
WHO WERE SAYING HOW RIDICULOUS
YOU SOUND SAYING THIS IS NOT MY
ERA.
THIS GOES BACK TO THE MEGYN
KELLY COMMENTS SAYING SANTA IS
NOT WHITE.
WE CAN LOOK AT THE DISNEY
PRINCESSES AND THEY ALL LOOK THE
SAME.
EVEN AMONG THE WHITE PRINCESSES
THEY ALL LOOK THE SAME.
THERE'S NEVER BEEN A DISABLED
PRINCESS OR OVERWEIGHT PRINCESS.
THERE'S SO MANY AREAS WE CAN
GROW AND LEARN IN THESE SPACES
'TO THE YOUR POINT, IT'S A
CARTOON CHARACTER CREDITOR YOU
IDIOTS, WHAT ARE YOU UPSET
ABOUT?
YOU HAVE SOUND SO RIDICULOUS.
>> I NEVER -- I NEVER DISAGREE
WITH ANYTHING THAT TIFFANY SAYS,
BUT SANTA IS REAL, HIS NAME IS
LARRY, WE'VE HAD HIM ON THE SHOW
TWICE.
SO I'M JUST SAYING, SANTA AS
REAL, DON'T PLAY WITH ME WITH
SANTA BECAUSE I MET HIM, OKAY.
>> I CAN SAY ABOUT HALLIE
BAILEY, THIS GIRL IS SO
TALENTED.
HER AND HER SISTER, THEY WRITE
MUSIC, THEY UNDERSTAND MUSIC,
THEY'RE PART OF THE BEYONCE
FAMILY WHICH YOU KNOW I'M THE
HONORARY PRESIDENT OF THE BEE
ONSIS?
>> I DID KNOW THAT.
>> CHRIS, YOU'RE MY HONARY
COCHAIR OF THE BEYONCE FAN CLUB.
SHE'S SO TALENTED.
IF THERE'S ONE SAD THING TO BE
TAKEN AWAY, IT'S THAT HER JOY
WAS TAKEN AWAY BECAUSE OF THESE
FRINGE CRAZY PEOPLE TWEETING
THESE THINGS.
>> I THINK THE FINGER POINTING,
IT SHOULD GO TOWARDS HOLLYWOOD
AND THE FACT THAT OVERTHE PAST,
YOU KNOW, SINCE 1937 AND DISNEY
FILMS WE'VE SEEN SNOW WHITE AND
CINDERELLA AND SLEEPING BEAUTY
AND THEY'VE ALL LOOKED THE SAME,
AS YOU SAID.
SO I THINK IT'S HIGH TIME THAT
HOLLYWOOD BEGINS TO EMBRACE AND
OPEN DOORS AND ALLOW CREATIVES
THAT HAVE THESE STORIES TO TELL.
>> EXACTLY.
>> THEY CAN CREATE NEW STORIES.
MAYBE IT'S NOT GOING TO BE
ARIEL, MAYBE IT WILL BE A BLACK
PRIB SAYS WHO LIVES IN HARLEM OR
BROOKLYN.
WE NEED TO SEE MORE NEW STORIES.
>> AND BY THE WAY, THE PEOPLE
SORT OF OVERALL, THIS COMES TO
THE OVERALL TRAUMA THAT PEOPLE
ARE FEELING ABOUT THE CHANGES IN
THE CULTURE AND THAT THE CULTURE
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE THEM ANYMORE,
THAT THEY'RE NOT IN THE CENTER.
THIS IS ALL A BIGGER PICTURE.
WE WANTED TO TALK ABOUT THIS
BECAUSE THERE IS A BIGGER
PICTURE.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
COMING UP, MORE AM JOY AFTER THE
BREAK.
UP, MORE AM JOY AFTER THE
ave moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis,
month after month,
the clock is ticking on
irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
HUMIRA can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
HUMIRA targets and blocks a
source of inflammation
that contributes to joint pain
and irreversible damage.
HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections
including tuberculosis,
and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened;
as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor if
you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Help stop the clock
on further irreversible
joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here. Right now.
HUMIRA.