♪♪
NARRATOR:
Funding for "American Masters"
is provided by...
the Corporation
for Public Broadcasting...
Support for this program
also provided by
the National Endowment
for the Arts.
Art works.
The Paul W. Zuccaire Foundation,
and by contributions to your PBS
station from viewers like you.
Thank you.
-You know, just gather around
quietly. Come on.
Now, just stand by.
Here he is now.
Say, Fats, a bunch of the kids
would like to listen
to you blowin' up a storm.
Would you let them listen in?
-Well, as a rule
we don't do it.
But for the kids,
I'm more than glad.
-Hooray.
-♪ I like the way you walk ♪
♪ I like to
hear you talk ♪
♪ Let me hold your hand ♪
♪ And try to understand ♪
♪ I want a girl like you ♪
♪ Tell my trouble to ♪
♪ Don't be afraid ♪
♪ You've heard what I said ♪
MAN: Fats,
how'd this rock 'n' roll
all get started, anyway?
-Well, what they call
rock 'n' roll
now is rhythm and blues.
I've been playin'
for 15 years in New Orleans.
♪ I love you the best ♪
♪ Let the four winds blow ♪
-NARRATOR: A native son
of New Orleans, Fats Domino
would pioneer the big beat sound
and become one of the world's
most beloved entertainers.
[Instrumental]
Antoine Domino, Jr.,
arrived on February 26, 1928,
delivered by a midwife
with the assistance
of his grandmother, Carmelite,
who had been born into slavery.
Antoine Jr. was the last
of eight Domino children
and the only one to be born
in New Orleans.
-MAN: The -- the neighborhood
that Fats Domino grew up in
is called the Lower Ninth Ward
in New Orleans.
And it's arguably where a lot
of the best musicians came from.
And it's a part of the city
that enjoys a reputation
in New Orleans for being...
That's the -- the heart, really,
the heartbeat of the city.
-MAN: It was almost
like another, uh,
world, like another world.
There was always talk about...
When you talked
about the Lower Ninth Ward,
you talk as if the people
who lived down there
didn't have as much goin' on
as the people mid-city.
Of course, some of the people
who lived down there had a lot
goin' on.
-DOMINO: I was born
on Jourdan Avenue down here
in the Ninth Ward.
They said I was born in a house
at 1939 Jourdan Avenue.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I went to a school
right down the street here.
It was about 10 blocks
from here, McCartey School.
And then I remember years
ago when I used --
used to come home from school.
My mom used to be cooking, um,
on a wood stove.
And sometimes I
got from school, uh,
and I had to cut wood
that evening.
Another thing I remember
when I lived on Jourdan Avenue,
I used to pick iron and copper
in the street, Jourdan Avenue,
I used to live on.
The street was so bad,
the holes were so big
they used to get stuff
from the cotton bale and --
and and fill the street up
with nothin' but tin and iron.
That -- that's the way
Jourdan Avenue was.
And I used to sell it
to -- sell the scrap.
If you made your 20 cents
or 25 cents livin'...
That was a lot of money,
25 cents, in that time.
-When he got out
and about, he was,
uh, roamin' the streets
of the Ninth Ward.
And he would love to pick up
things that he'd see.
And sometimes he'd sell 'em
to the junkman who,
uh, ironically,
would become part
of the song "The Junker's Blues"
that he'd later record.
His life was changed, basically,
when his sister
married Harrison Verrett,
who was a, uh, relatively
well-known New Orleans musician
who played banjo.
♪♪
-DOMINO: My brother-in-law
Harrison used to play
with Papa Celestin Band.
You know, and, uh, one time
I went to the French Quarter,
and I heard them play out
there several times.
That's where I really learned
from my brother-in-law,
Harrison Verrett.
He had a lot of patience.
He would take...
He -- he just loved bein'
with children, you know?
And that's
what I loved about him.
-COLEMAN: Fats had always played
around on the family piano
since they had bought it.
First of all,
they put it out in the garage
to keep him from, uh,
drivin' them crazy a little bit.
But he even quit school
because he wanted
to play the piano so much.
And, uh, so he only went
to the fourth grade.
Harrison actually taught him
how to play it.
And he put the notes
on the piano on pieces of tape.
And it was a beat-up piano.
You could actually see the metal
through the -- the ivory.
But, uh, Fats, you know,
got some sound out of it.
-DOMINO: We had an upright piano
in the house.
He'd teach me the chords,
the foundation.
If you know
how to play the chord,
he'd write the chord
down to you.
And you play this famous song,
playin' in the band,
just by the chord.
And after I learnt that, that's
when I just went on my own.
Everybody had a piano.
I used to stop.
And the -- the manager said,
"Where's Fats at?"
His son would say...
His son was Willie.
Willie'd say, "I don't know."
Say, "Well,
you got a piano over there.
You better go look. He might be
where you left the piano.
Where the piano at,
where Fats at."
-COLEMAN: From the late
'30s to the '40s,
Fats started listening
more to jukeboxes.
That's basically the way that
blacks heard music in those days
because not a lot of 'em
had record players.
There was no radio that
played black music at that time.
[Upbeat music playing]
Fats' primary love for music
was in the boogie-woogie
piano players.
He always listened to
Meade Lux Lewis
and Pete Johnson,
the great piano players.
His cousins had a, uh, bar.
And he actually not only
had a jukebox there,
he also had a sounding machine,
which was I guess kind
of a luxury in those days.
The one
he particularly remembered,
I think it was a video
called Low Down Dog.
It was actually a comedian
who was found his woman
foolin' around with different
guy in the kitchen, okay,
and somethin' like that.
And he -- he chased her.
And he -- he started
singin' this song,
pointin' his finger
at her sayin',
"I ain't gonna be your
low-down dog no more."
-♪ I ain't gonna be your
low-down dog no more ♪
♪ Ain't gonna be
your low-down dog no more ♪
-COLEMAN: People that knew it
at the time was Joe Turner
who was singin'.
He was just mimin' the song.
And was Pete Johnson who was
playin' the boogie-woogie piano.
-♪ Work all day,
don't you know, my babe ♪
-Fats loved that video.
And he actually started playing
"Low Down Dog."
And he kept playin' it
for the next half a century.
♪♪
-♪ Ooh wee ♪
♪ Oo-ooh wee ♪
♪ It's a low down shame... ♪
CLEARY: It's very hard
to find out
what his formative
influences are.
Basic blues,
old-style blues piano.
It's -- and it's --
And boogie-woogie, I mean, that,
you know, that --
Straight-up boogie-woogie.
-♪ Bad, bad whiskey ♪
♪ Bad, bad whiskey ♪
♪ Bad, bad whiskey
made me lose my happy home ♪
-COLEMAN: Another favorite
performer of Fats'
was Amos Milburn, who was
a great boogie-woogie player.
Amos played these
low-down blues.
And they were all really sexy.
Fats played blues
like Amos Milburn.
Another influence of Fats'
was Louis Jordan,
who was the most popular
black singer-performer
of the 1940s.
And he was famous
for all of his novelty songs.
But more significantly,
he did some songs
that I would almost consider
rockers, like "Caldonia."
♪♪
-♪ Walkin' with my baby ♪
♪ She got great, big feet ♪
♪ She's long, lean and lanky ♪
♪ And ain't had
nothin' to eat ♪
♪ But she's my baby ♪
♪ And I love her just the same ♪
♪ Crazy about that woman ♪
♪ 'Cause Caldonia is her name ♪
-COLEMAN: He's shouting.
And he's -- and he's playing
this heavy boogie-woogie beat.
And so that was a song that
almost everybody in New Orleans
played at one time or another.
-♪ I've always loved you, baby ♪
♪ 'Cause Caldonia is your name ♪
-COLEMAN: After Fats
started playing in the little
Ninth Ward clubs,
he started running
into different people
who would be influential
in his career.
The first one was probably
Billy Diamond,
who was a local band leader.
He was a bass player.
He was a little short go-getter.
Fats told me during those days,
Billy Diamond was the only
person who could find a gig.
Uh, he could find a gig
when nobody else could.
-I gave him
the name Fats before then,
before he even had a record.
I gave him the name Fats
after a guy named Fat Waller
back in them days.
He was a great piano player.
He got mad when I played piano,
called him fat.
"Don't call me fat.
Don't call me fat, brown boy.
I don't know
what you callin' me fat for.
I don't call you Fat Billy."
-NARRATOR: While Fats
was pounding out boogie-woogie
with Billy Diamond's Band
at the Hideaway
and other neighborhood clubs,
a New Orleans trumpet sensation
by the name of Dave Bartholomew
was on a roll.
-COLEMAN: Dave Bartholomew
was one of the most popular,
if not the most popular,
band leader in the city.
And occasionally Fats went
and see him and check him out.
Earl Palmer, who was, uh,
Dave's great drummer,
had him sit in one time.
Fats got up there
and played that little jam
and boogie-woogie,
"Swanee River Boogie,"
or whatever it was,
and maybe another song or two.
Dave Bartholomew
did not like that.
As a matter of fact,
he came up to Earl Palmer
and said afterwards,
"I thought I told you
not to let that guy sit in."
Of course, he had no clue
that they would have
a incredible history to come,
as far as making some
of the most influential records
in the next 10 or 15 years.
-NARRATOR: One night,
Bartholomew brought a man
from Imperial Records,
a Mr. Lew Chudd,
to see Fats perform
at a local club.
-DOMINO: I work at the Hideaway.
I was real famous
at the Hideaway for just playin'
other people number.
Dave and Lew Chudd
came down there one night.
Lew Chudd wanted to hear
me sing and play.
So I did.
-COLEMAN: Fats played
"The Junker's Blues."
-♪ They call,
they call me a junker ♪
-COLEMAN: Champion Jack Dupree
was the barrelhouse piano player
from New Orleans who recorded
the original version
of "The Junker Blues" in 1940
and had a, you know,
mild success with it.
And that was a song that really
sold Fats to Lew Chudd.
Lew said, "You know,
I gotta have this guy."
And he actually signed him
right there on the spot
that very night.
-DOMINO: And about a week later,
say about 2 weeks later,
we had got together
to record the first record,
"Fat Man," 1949.
-And we never looked back
for 25 years.
[Upbeat piano]
-Dave said, "We gonna record
'The Fat Man.'"
I said, "We are?"
Oh, I got excited.
Durin' that period of time,
we had a radio program,
"The Fat Man."
So when we got in the studio,
Dave said, "This is Fats,
The Fat Man."
I look at Dave, said, "Dave,
The Fat Man is a white man."
-♪ They call,
they call me The Fat Man ♪
♪ 'Cause I weigh 200 pounds ♪
♪ All the girls, they love me ♪
♪ 'Cause I know my way around ♪
♪ I was standin' ♪
♪ I was standin' on the corner ♪
♪ Of Rampart and Canal ♪
♪ I was watchin', watchin' ♪
♪ Watchin' all the Creole gals ♪
[Vocalizing]
-"Fat Man," the first hit
that he -- hit that he had,
the first record in 1949, was
basically "The Junker's Blues."
And he told me
this the other day.
He said, I asked him
about "The Fat Man. "
He said, "It's just
The Junker's Blues.
I just changed it to...
From 'they call me a junker,'
to --
to, 'they call me The Fat Man'."
♪♪
-Fats played it
as if it was his own.
It was very final
when Fats played.
If you had never heard
whoever played the original,
if you heard Fats Domino's
version, that was enough.
You can just take it from there.
♪♪
-So I would say,
"What we gonna call him?"
I said, "Hell,
we gonna call him Fat Man."
♪♪
As soon as they heard it,
that was it.
♪♪
♪ I'm goin', I'm goin',
goin' away ♪
♪ And then I'm
goin', goin' to stay ♪
♪ 'Cause women and a bad life ♪
♪ They're carryin'
this soul away ♪
-NARRATOR: With "The Fat Man"
rising to number one
in the February 1950 rhythm
and blues charts,
Lew Chudd's hunch had paid off.
He quickly reassembled Fats
with Dave Bartholomew and band
for additional sessions
at Cosimo Matassa's
Rampart Street studio.
Cosimo's J&M Music Shop was the
only recording studio in town
and was quickly becoming
the Mecca for record men
looking to cash in on
the New Orleans
rhythm and blues sound.
And Dave Bartholomew's little
orchestra became the house band
backing nearly every performance
recorded there.
-New Orleans produces a
disproportionately large amount
of talented musicians.
And it really comes up
with the raw material.
-MAN: It's the only place
in the world
where everybody,
even white listeners,
clap on two and four instead
of one and three.
Right away, you can tell if
a white dude's from New Orleans,
man, when you hear him clap.
He's on the beat.
And that's --
that's kind of, uh,
a -- a natural thing
with New Orleans people.
You got kids in the street,
man... It's a lot of talent,
musically,
if you stand on a certain way.
Well, look at the history
of the town.
There's always been music.
That's maybe why you're born
with a lot of it
instilled in you.
-You can call it the big beat,
the sweet beat whatever it is.
But New Orleans got the beat.
-There have always been
gigs in New Orleans.
There's only really
a few periods in the history
of New Orleans
in the 20th century where
there's been a really thriving
recording scene.
And, um, the fact
that there was is largely due
to Dave Bartholomew
and Cosimo Matassa.
♪♪
-TOUSSAINT: Cosimo Matassa
and Dave Bartholomew
put New Orleans on the map.
-The room was 15-by-16.
I started recording direct
to disk, which,
uh, had a couple
of good features about it.
For one thing,
you didn't do any editing.
You didn't do any pickups.
You didn't do any overdubbing.
You played the damn thing
from beginning to end.
And -- and that made
for performance.
And I think that helped me.
I started on the fact that
everybody performed together
beginning to end.
Had to be right.
I always, 'til today,
thought that my job
was to put on disk
what was happening out
in the studio.
It was OJT, as Dave told me --
"on the job training."
-Imperial wanted us to go
on a tour
after Fats' first record,
which was "Fat Man Blues."
The other side
was "Detroit City Blues."
We had 3 days...
It was late startin'
this tour 'cause
Fats would hide every time
we go to look for him 'cause
he was afraid to go on the tour.
He was, you know, shook up.
First time
he'd ever went on any tour.
And we -- we got to go on --
go with us on the trip
was Professor Longhair.
-I got nothin'
but stars with me:
Lee Allen, Professor Longhair,
Fat Domino, Dave Bartholomew,
Bob Foreman, Frank Fields.
We're playin' in a dump.
At 11:30, 12:00,
I said, "Wasn't he supposed to
pay me at intermission?"
Earl Palmer say, "I seen
that man go out the door."
I said, "Well, he goin' home
to get the money."
That been 40 years.
He ain't come back yet.
[Laughs]
♪♪
[Whistling]
-NARRATOR:
Between 1950 and 1955,
Fats recorded a steady stream
of singles for Imperial
with many of them charting high
in the R&B charts.
Things were buzzing
at Cosimo's studio.
And Dave Bartholomew
was the go-to guy
for all the record labels
wishing to record
in New Orleans.
♪ Well, I'm goin' to
New Orleans ♪
♪ I'm goin' to see
the Mardi Gras ♪
♪ Well, I'm goin' to
New Orleans ♪
♪ I'm goin' to see
the Mardi Gras ♪
♪ When I get to New Orleans ♪
♪ I want to know
what's carnival for ♪
[Whistling]
-NARRATOR:
He produced the sessions,
wrote the arrangements,
and used his band
to back the performers.
-He was the man number one.
He was the boss
with the hot sauce.
MATASSA: We didn't call
him The Chief for nothin'.
He was the chief.
He kept us focused,
and particularly people
like Fats he kept focused
because Fats tended to doodle
and ramble and -- and --
and that sort of thing.
I think, uh,
without a Dave,
there might not have been a Fats
in the national sense of it.
[Cheering and applause]
-DOMINO: Thank you.
-COLEMAN: Fats showed up in
his Cadillac at Cosimo's studio.
And Dave was cutting a session
with Lloyd Price.
And the piano player at the time
in Dave's band --
I think it was
Salvador Doucette --
was not really
cutting the triplets too well.
And so Fats was the perfect
answer to that problem.
And he asked Fats
if he would sit in.
And then he
played that amazing introduction
to "Lawdy Miss Clawdy."
♪♪
And then the triplets
and then a -- a solo
in the middle.
And it... "Lawdy Miss Clawdy"
became the biggest hit
of the year and knocked his own
number one, "Goin' Home,"
out of the charts.
[Playing]
-I think I played on that one.
-MAN: Yeah, you did.
-MAN: Yeah.
-Yeah. You did.
-MAN: And here it is,
"Alan Freed's
Rock 'n' Roll Party."
And here he is in person:
Alan Freed.
[Cheers and applause]
-Hello, everybody.
How are y'all?
Welcome to our rock 'n' roll
jubilee of stars.
And here we go to rockin'
with wailin' tenorman,
Freddy Mitchell
and the rock 'n' roll boogie!
Here we go.
-COLEMAN: Alan Freed had
actually started using
the phrase "rock 'n' roll"
at the end of 1954.
And the first ever so-called
rock 'n' roll concert
was his show in New York,
January of '55.
And it was an all-black show.
Alan Freed was using
the phrase rock 'n' roll
to popularize rhythm and blues
primarily with white teenagers.
-♪ Oh well good-bye ♪
♪ Although I'll cry ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
♪ You're the one to blame ♪
-COLEMAN: And so this --
this crossing point
was very significant
because Fats Domino came along
with his biggest hit ever.
And, of course,
that was "Ain't That a Shame."
-♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
♪ You're the one to blame ♪
♪ You broke my heart ♪
♪ When you said we'll part ♪
-That's nothing.
That was one sentence.
"Ain't That a Shame," it don't
have no bridge to it, no middle.
It's the same, uh, sentence
over and over again.
But we sold it with --
with the music.
Duh-duh, duh-dum, boom.
In other words, I had the whole
band playin' like a bass.
Boom, boom.
-♪ Me cry ♪
♪ When you said goodbye ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
-COLEMAN: It was also one
of his simplest songs ever.
If you listen to "Ain't
That a Shame," you'll see,
"You made me cry
when you said goodbye."
And that's actually
a classic Fats Domino lyric
because he --
he just wrote things in the most
simple terms possible.
-DOMINO: I remember them tellin'
me, "Your record goin' pop."
I didn't know
what he was talkin' about.
Lew Chudd,
see, "The record goin' pop.
You got a big record."
Well, I'm like...
We had sellers before.
"Goin' Home," "The Fat Man,"
you know --
that's what broke me through
everybody buyin' my record,
black and the white.
He say,
"You got a big one now."
♪ Tears fell like rain ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
-NARRATOR: The surprise success
of "Ain't That a Shame"
was a game-changer for both Fats
and Imperial Records.
Though finally achieving
a crossover hit
that was selling phenomenally to
both black and white audiences,
Dave and Fats could not have
predicted what would happen
within a week of its release.
♪♪
♪ You make me cry ♪
♪ When you said goodbye ♪
♪ Ain't that a shame ♪
♪ My tears fell like rain ♪
-DOMINO: Mine was not a week.
Somebody told me, you know,
a fellow by the name
of Pat Boone
comin' out with your record
next week.
Hollerin' somethin' crazy.
-And Pat Boone
was a very, um, innocent,
white crooner, should we say.
And, uh, he just was kind of,
uh, you know,
tryin' to croon a song
that should have been a rocker.
-Keep in mind,
it was him, you know.
A lot of people wasn't gonna
buy us at all because we
were black, at that time.
You know, there was segregation
in music too.
I know that, you know,
"I don't wanna hear it."
But after they heard it a while,
it started growin' on you,
and that's it,
like anything else.
-DOMINO: He did it all right.
It sold a lot of records.
-NARRATOR: While
"Ain't That a Shame"
was burning up the 1955
R&B and pop charts,
other black artists
such as Chuck Berry
and Little Richard
were following Fats' lead.
-♪ Woo, hoo, hoo, hoo baby ♪
♪ Havin' me some fun tonight ♪
-NARRATOR: The rock 'n' roll era
had begun.
-MAN: Rolling master A.
Master A, take one.
♪♪
[Applause]
-NARRATOR: By early 1956,
Elvis Presley was the king
of the pop charts.
-♪ You know I can be found ♪
♪ Sitting home all alone ♪
-NARRATOR: Rockers Bill Haley
and the Comets,
Gene Vincent,
and Carl Perkins
were also grabbing the attention
of the nation's youth.
By March of 1956,
Fats' "I'm in Love Again"
became his second
top-10 hit.
Dave Bartholomew's big beat
was making Antoine Domino
a very famous man.
-♪ Yes, it's me,
and I'm in love again ♪
♪ Had no lovin'
since you know when ♪
♪ You know I love you,
yes I do ♪
♪ And I'm savin' all my lovin'
just for you ♪
♪ I need your lovin',
and I need it bad ♪
♪ Just like a dog
when he's goin' mad ♪
♪ Whoa-wee, baby, whoa-wee ♪
♪ Baby, won't you give your love
to me ♪
♪ Eeny-meeny and miney-mo ♪
♪ Told me you didn't want me
around no more ♪
♪ Whoa-wee, baby, whoa-wee ♪
♪ Baby, don't you let
your dog bite me ♪
[Instrumental]
♪ Yes, it's me,
and I'm in love again ♪
♪ Had no lovin'
since you know when ♪
♪ You know I love you,
yes I do ♪
♪ And I'm savin' all my lovin'
just for you ♪
♪ Eeny-meeny and miney-mo ♪
♪ Told me you didn't want me
around no more ♪
♪ Whoa-wee, baby, whoa-wee ♪
♪ Baby, don't you let
your dog bite me ♪
[Instrumental ending]
-NARRATOR: The year 1956
belonged to Fats Domino.
With nine records scoring
in the top-10
pop and rhythm and blues charts,
there was no stopping him.
And in that year,
he recorded the song for which
he will be forever remembered.
-♪ I found my thrill ♪
♪ On Blueberry Hill ♪
-COLEMAN: "Blueberry Hill"
was a pop standard
that had originally been
recorded in 1940
by Gene Autry
for a singin' cowboy movie.
But the most significant version
for Fats
was the Louis Armstrong version.
It was a phenomenal time
for him.
The unfortunate thing is that
Lew Chudd of Imperial Records
actually tried too hard to sell
Fats Domino to a white audience.
He thought that if you made
it sound more pop,
it would sell more white.
But he kind of missed the point
of Fats Domino.
And so he was having him record
all these standards.
Some worked, some didn't.
As "Blueberry Hill" proved,
when Fats redid
a standard,
he changed it all around
so the people
that knew the old standard,
they barely recognized it.
-And the rest is history.
A record that has,
I've been told,
sold over 5 1/2 million records,
"Blueberry Hill."
And of course,
his number one record
of all time.
♪ I found my thrill ♪
♪ On Blueberry Hill ♪
♪ When I found you ♪
♪ The moon stood still ♪
♪ On Blueberry Hill ♪
♪ And lingered until ♪
♪ My dream came... ♪
♪ The wind in the willow
played ♪
♪ Love's sweet melody ♪
♪ But all of the vows we made ♪
♪ Were never to be ♪
♪ Though we're apart ♪
♪ You're part of me still ♪
♪ For you were my thrill ♪
♪ On Blueberry Hill ♪
♪ The wind in the willow
played ♪
♪ Love's sweet melody ♪
♪ But all of the vows we made ♪
♪ Were never to be ♪
♪ Though we're apart ♪
♪ You're part of me still ♪
♪ For you were my thrill ♪
♪ On Blueberry Hill ♪
-COLEMAN: He had an amazing
string of success at that time.
But with "Blueberry Hill,"
"Blue Monday"
and "I'm Walkin',"
Fats had three huge hits
at the time.
Even Time magazine
recognized it.
He was huge.
He -- he was actually
headlining the biggest shows
in rock 'n' roll at that time.
People like Chuck Berry,
Little Richard, Buddy Holly,
the Everly Brothers
and Jerry Lee Lewis
were all underneath Fats.
They did not even approach
his record sales at that time.
He was selling a million records
every month.
-RAY: There was a time
he and Elvis Presley,
for a year or two there,
were neck and neck in sales.
People don't realize this.
-♪ I'm beat to my socks ♪
♪ My gal calls,
got to tell her that I'm out ♪
♪ 'Cause Thursday
is a hard workin' day ♪
♪ And Friday I get my pay ♪
-HARDESTY:
We did it in California.
And --
and recordin' "Blue Monday,"
they had another saxophone
player playin' the baritone.
He... Fats didn't like the way
he soloed on it.
He said, "Herbert, I
want you to play the baritone."
You want me
to play the baritone?
I got my tenor here.
He said, "No, please,
play the solo on baritone."
So I played the solo
on baritone.
And he went wild.
And the, uh, people love it,
like the da, da, da-da.
Let me see if I can play it
on my saxophone.
I don't have my strap.
[Playing]
♪♪
-"Blue Monday,"
I think that's one
of the greatest things
I ever wrote.
♪♪
-♪ Saturday mornin',
oh Saturday mornin' ♪
♪ All my tiredness
has gone away ♪
♪ Got my money and my honey ♪
♪ And I'm out on the stand
to play ♪
♪ Sunday mornin'
my head is bad ♪
♪ But it's worth it for
the times that I've had ♪
♪ But I've got to get my rest ♪
♪ 'Cause Monday's a mess ♪
♪ The big beat keep you rockin'
in your seat ♪
-NARRATOR: By the end of 1956,
all of the major
television networks
and Hollywood began to call.
And the entire nation
was tuning in.
-♪ The sun's gonna shine ♪
♪ In my back door some day ♪
♪ Just you wait and see ♪
♪ Girl can't help it ♪
♪ She was born to please ♪
♪ Can't help it, the girl
can't help it ♪
♪ And she's got a figure
made to squeeze ♪
♪ Can't help it, the girl
can't help it ♪
♪ And she's got a figure
made to squeeze ♪
♪ Can't help it, the girl
can't help it ♪
-Let's face it,
rhythm and blues, uh, is here.
So we have a man here today
who is just
about the hottest attraction
in that field.
As a matter of fact,
I have a -- have a little award
to present to him a bit later,
something I don't know
if he knows about yet.
The one and only Fats Domino.
-♪ When my dreamboat
comes home ♪
-BARTHOLOMEW: You wanna make
a good impression
because this means an awful lot
to you
to be on those type of shows.
You're not only help -- helpin'
them, you're helpin' yourself,
gettin' yourself exposure
all over the world.
So you think about that.
And you wanna do the best
you can.
-When Fats appeared on
network TV show,
it increased sales tremendously.
-Uh, Fats, as you know,
is one of our great disciples
of rock 'n' roll.
And Fats, according
to a clipping in "Down Beat,"
Dizzy Gillespie just
finished a tour
in the Middle East
where he was a smash.
-DOMINO: Crazy, man.
-And Louis Armstrong
was a big hit in South Africa.
-DOMINO: Crazy, man.
-And a rumor has it that
you're going to
introduce rock 'n' roll
to Alaska.
-DOMINO: Cool, man.
♪ I'm walkin', yes indeed ♪
♪ And I'm talkin'
about you and me ♪
♪ And I'm hopin'
you'll ask me back again ♪
-♪ I'm flyin', I'm flyin' high ♪
♪ I'm shy, me, oh, my ♪
♪ I'm hopin' you'll ask me
back again, again ♪
-♪ What you gonna do
when the well runs dry ♪
♪ You gonna run away tonight ♪
♪ I'm gonna run right by your
side ♪
♪ For you, Perry Como,
I'd even die ♪
♪♪
-COLEMAN: This is
November 18, 1956,
a very significant date,
a very cold night
in New York City
when Ed Sullivan
announced Fats Domino.
-ANNOUNCER:
"The Ed Sullivan Show."
-I had a lot
of respect for him.
He spent a lot of time with us.
He -- he -- he gave us his all.
And you know what I mean.
He would be with us
all day long.
And -- and that wasn't all.
And then he had us as many times
that we wanted to.
-...New Orleans,
another...
Well, he's had so many.
This... He's had 1 million
record, million sales record.
Here is Fats Domino
singing "Blueberry Hill."
So, let's hear it...
[Playing]
-COLEMAN: He put Fats' band
behind a curtain.
And he put Fats just playing
the piano by himself,
which was a very strange thing
for Fats.
And then even stranger was
at the very end of the show --
of the song, I should say,
Fats stood up.
It was kind of like Ed Sullivan
wanted people to see
how chubby he was so that,
you know, he looks harmless.
♪♪
-♪ For you were my thrill ♪
-One of the great record stars,
high on the list of all hits
in the country today,
is a very happy, little,
rotund fellow named Fats Domino.
-That was the beginning
of the "harmless
Fats Domino" mythology,
which still continues
to some degree today.
-Well, Fats, I have this
surprise for you now.
This is from "Cash Box,"
one of the important, uh, record
industry, uh, trade papers.
And they want you
to have this award
because you've been voted
by the Disc Jockeys of America
the most programmed
rhythm and blues male vocalist
of the year 1956.
Congratulations.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
-NARRATOR: In 1957,
the Fats Domino band
traveled 30,000 miles
around the country,
working a total of 355 shows
and selling out nightclubs
and concert halls
everywhere they ventured.
-ALLEN: He was one
of the biggest stars out.
There was no other bigger star
than Fats in --
in the rock 'n' roll field.
-MAN: We -- we got to knock
and push 'em off of us.
You know, I mean, you know,
they --
they was just somethin' else.
They knock down the walls
to get to Fats Domino.
I'm not kiddin'.
They really did.
-RAY: I did a lot of travelin'.
Nothin' like bein'
with Fats Domino.
We'd drive and drive.
And I keep sayin', "Well,
aren't we gonna stop for lunch?
Aren't we gonna --
are we gonna eat?"
-McLEAN: You know, him and
his brother came in the house
and said, "No, we want
you to come and go to
Pensacola,
Florida with us.
We got to be there tonight."
I say, "It's Christmas.
I don't wanna go nowhere."
And you know what happened?
They took and carried me
and picked me up,
I'm helpless,
and put me on the bus.
And, you know, I was in Florida.
-BARTHOLOMEW:
That was my life out there.
A lot of times we was doin'
them one nighters,
all night long sleepin' in the
car and all that kinda (bleep).
-HARDESTY: The most fun was
after we got off in the hotels.
There was party,
party, party, parties goin'
on from the bottom
to the top floor.
-NARRATOR: With Fats'
enormous popularity,
promoters had little trouble
filling concert halls
and ballrooms to capacity.
White and black fans
clamored to see Fats live,
sometimes
with explosive results.
-COLEMAN: He had more riots
than any other
rock 'n' roller,
uh, maybe ever.
He had four major riots
at his shows,
partly because of integration
but also the fact that they
had alcohol at these shows.
So they were mixing alcohol
plus dancing
plus the races together
for the first time
in a lot of these places.
And it was leading
to a little fights
which soon bloomed
into huge fights.
And they called the police.
-HARDESTY: We got caught
in two riots.
And it wasn't --
it wasn't a racial thing.
There was a fight.
And with -- within the fight,
the police decided to throw
tear gas in the hall.
And everybody panic.
Well, it turned out
not to be a riot,
but people tryin'
to escape --
tryin' to get away from
the tear gas.
When they started broadcastin'
that there was --
where Fats Domino was playin'
and there was a race riot,
that was a $1 million
exposure right there.
All the news media picked it up.
So that was publicity.
But there...
It wasn't a real race riot.
-COMO: Fats, this
rock 'n' roll music seems to be
under an awful heavy attack
from all over the country.
There's been riots.
It's been banned
in certain parts of this country
and abroad.
You know of any reason for that?
-Well, as far as I know,
music make people happy.
I know it make me happy.
-COMO: You wouldn't blame it
on rock 'n' roll.
-No, indeed.
-What happened up in
Rhode Island
where you where playin'?
-Well, you know how it is when
the Navy and Marines
get together.
-You don't think
it was the music?
-No, couldn't be.
-NARRATOR: Life on the road
for an African-American
rock 'n' roll band, even
the country's most popular one,
was mired in the
pre-Civil Rights mores
of the day.
-DOMINO: Sometimes we used
to go up 100 mile out the way
to get a place to sleep.
-It was tough. We stayed in
little, small-like hotels.
We didn't have the privilege
and the -- the restaurants.
I started drivin' the bus.
And I would go
into these restaurants
or these places
and sort of help integration
along to push things, you know?
And when the hotels
first integrated, that was --
I was the first ones in them.
-Well, I think there is, uh,
no doubt about the fact that,
uh, the Negro
is more determined now than
ever before to be free.
I think that there is
a discontent
in the Negro community,
a frustration and an impatience,
if we can use that word, uh,
that we haven't seen before.
I've been around the country
for the last few days,
uh, speaking.
And I don't think
I've ever seen, uh,
the Negro population
of our nation
more aroused and more determined
as I've seen
on these particular trips.
-DIAMOND: Before
Martin Luther King got killed,
Fats was in that same hotel
2 weeks before then
playin' for the --
the garbage workers there.
He'd bring the --
the workers together when --
whenever he'd play,
white and black.
It's somethin' about his person
that draw a lot
of people in, you know.
-MAN: Once it was recognized,
once it accepted,
and once the -- the audience,
the people
started wantin' this music,
there was nothin'
that the radio stations
or television can do about it.
They had to accept it.
-COLEMAN: So there was
this historic moment
in American history
that -- that things
were kind of coming together.
And people don't really
credit rock 'n' roll
with integrating America.
But it really did.
-NARRATOR: Constantly far away
from his loving family
and his Ninth Ward home,
life on the road
was beginning to take its toll.
-DOMINO: Anybody,
when you first leave home,
especially New Orleans,
you still got your home
on your mind.
And the whole band is like that.
Every time I had a Monday night
off, I usually fly home.
-NARRATOR: Although he
received the adulation
of millions of fans,
Fats always longed to be
on that last stretch of highway
that led to the city he loved.
-♪ This time
I'm walkin' to New Orleans ♪
♪ I'm walkin' to New Orleans ♪
♪ I'm gonna need
two pair of shoes ♪
♪ When I get through walkin'
these blues ♪
♪ When I get back to
New Orleans ♪
♪ I've got my suitcase
in my hand ♪
♪ Now ain't that a shame ♪
♪ I'm leavin' here today ♪
♪ Yes, I'm goin' back home
to stay ♪
♪ Yes, I'm walkin' to
New Orleans ♪
♪ You used to be my honey ♪
♪ 'Til I lost all
my money ♪
♪ No use for me to cry ♪
♪ I'll see you
by and by ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm walkin'
to New Orleans ♪
♪ And I got no time
for talkin' ♪
♪ I'm walkin' to New Orleans ♪
-NARRATOR: By the end of 1963,
a new generation of rockers,
many of whom idolized Fats,
were grabbing
the world's attention.
Although Fats
continued to record,
his top-10 hit records
were now well behind him.
For the next 40 years,
he brought the big beat
around the world,
performing his hits
at sold-out shows
from New Orleans to Japan.
-♪ I'm walkin' ♪
♪ Yes, indeed
I'm walkin' ♪
-NARRATOR: Up until his final
public performance in 2006,
Dave Bartholomew
and Herb Hardesty
were often in the band.
For 65 years,
Fats never departed
from his boogie-woogie roots
and always ended his shows
with a gumbo-spiced ode
to New Orleans --
"When the Saints
Go Marchin' In."
-♪ Oh, when the saints ♪
♪ Go marchin' in ♪
♪ Oh, when the saints
go marchin' in ♪
-BARTHOLOMEW: Always close
with the saints.
Sometimes we couldn't get off
the bandstand, we'd go back.
-♪ When the saints go
marchin' in ♪
♪ Oh, when the sun ♪
♪ Refused to shine ♪
♪ Oh, when the sun
refused to shine ♪
-A gentlemen.
When you work
with a man 50 years,
that should speak for itself.
♪ Oh, when the saints ♪
♪ Go marchin' in ♪
♪ Oh, when the saints
go marchin' in ♪
-The stories he told
was so charmin',
even when he was tellin'
a hard luck story.
A prince of a man.
-♪ Oh, when the sun ♪
♪ Refused to shine ♪
♪ Oh, when the sun
refused to shine ♪
♪ I say I want to be
in that number ♪
-Colleges and universities
that had courses
only on jazz artists.
I can... Why not on --
on -- on artists
like Fats or Chuck Berry?
I can never understand why
the cities that they represented
didn't recognize them
the same way
they would recognize
a Louis Armstrong.
-COLEMAN: John Lennon,
the first song
he ever learned
was "Ain't That a Shame."
First rock 'n' roll song
that George Harrison ever heard
was "I'm in Love Again."
And Paul McCartney's
just recorded a slew
of Fats Domino songs.
Uh, on top of that,
Elvis Presley once even called
Fats the king of rock 'n' roll.
Little Richard said
that he worshipped Fats
and was honored
to touch his hand.
And, of course,
he recorded most of his hits
with members of Fats' band.
-Here you have a formula
that they haven't had to change
in over half a century.
It's as good now as it was then.
The music business changes
every week.
Here is something
that you're witnessing
and listening to the same sound
that music lovers would have
been hearing half a century ago.
And it still does the trick.
It does the trick
because it's really good.
-Two Daves, I don't
think that would have worked.
Uh, two Fats wouldn't have
gotten off the ground.
Two Fats would have had to find
another one Dave somewhere.
♪♪
-I'm glad
I could join the elites
and just be one in a crowd.
Together we stand,
divided we fall.
♪♪
NARRATOR:
Funding for "American Masters"
is provided by...
the Corporation
for Public Broadcasting...
Support for this program
also provided by
the National Endowment
for the Arts.
Art works.
The Paul W. Zuccaire Foundation,
and by contributions to your PBS
station from viewers like you.
Thank you.
MAN: You know, just gather
around quietly. ♪♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
NARRATOR:
To learn more about Fats Domino
and other American Masters,
visit pbs.org/americanmasters,
or find us on Facebook, Twitter,
and Tumblr.
♪♪
"The Big Beat: Fats Domino
and the Birth of Rock 'n' Roll"
is available on DVD.
To order, visit shopPBS.org
or call 1-800-PLAY-PBS.
DOMINO: Whoo!
♪♪
MAN: Antoine, you know,
you still got it, man.
DOMINO: You -- You --
You still got it, too.
[ Both laugh ]
♪ ♪
BE MORE PBS
[Glasses clink]
Narrator: Looking for a
traditional-style butcher shop?
Head over to
Stachowski's market
for a true old-world experience.
Jamie, how you doing?
Mr. Jonas, how are you?
Good to see you.
Yeah. Nice to see
you as always.
It's a pleasure.
What's good?
Narrator: Owner and head butcher
Jamie Stachowski
brings some serious flair
to his Georgetown storefront.
Stachowski:
We're a throwback.
This just reminds people of some
time back in their history--
a custom butcher shop,
where you can find
a variety of meat products
and things to go along
with them.
[Sizzling]
That's what we've tried
to achieve here,
is a corner candy store
for carnivores.
And let's do some
scallopini.
Just slice it,
maybe pound it
a little for me.
All right, terrific.
All right, so let me
get this sliced up
and pounded.
Jonas: There just aren't
places like this anymore,
where you have a local butcher,
a local meat store.
This is like Paris.
This is like
the Italian countryside.
There's a little bit of it
right here in Georgetown.
There's a nice feeling
to the place.
Narrator: Stop by at lunch
for one of the market's
signature sandwiches,
like the hot pastrami
or 4-meat grinder.
Just don't plan on
finishing it anytime soon.
Man: Oh, no. You really can't
eat the grinder in one sitting.
And if you can, make him
president of the United States.
I was surprised
when I received it,
because I literally
could eat this all week long.
So we had to
have it cut in 4s
just for me to be able
to take a bite.
Stachowski: You travel to
the Polish neighborhood
where I'm from,
sandwiches were meals to us,
so they tended to be
on the big side.
Look, we are in Georgetown,
but we're tucked up away
in the Rose Park neighborhood.
So we gotta stand out,
and our sandwiches
let us do that.
Now we've gotten
the reputation for that.
Narrator: And if your
appetite isn't so big,
there are still a few items
on the menu that might be
just the ticket.
Sometimes if you don't
feel like you can handle
3 days' worth of sandwich,
might just need a salad!
Narrator: To learn more
about "Neighborhood Eats,"
visit WETA.org.
Narrator: To learn more
about "Neighborhood Eats,"
NARRATOR:
From Earth to space.
There's no tougher 50 miles
to cross.