Funding for "American Masters"
is provided by...
Support for this program
also provided by...
...and by contributions
to your PBS station
from viewers like you.
MAN: The world's greatest
blues singer,
the King of the Blues --
B.B. King!
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
FREEMAN: In 1925,
on a hot, sticky Wednesday
in the middle of September,
the cries of a newborn baby
rang out from
sharecropper's cabin
over the cotton fields
of the Mississippi Delta.
[ Baby crying ]
A boy was born that day
that was going to make
a difference.
His name -- Riley B. King.
[ Thunder rumbles ]
RAITT:
There's no music in the world
that cuts emotionally
the way that blues guitar
can cut.
G. BENSON: When you say "blues"
and you say "B.B. King,"
you've said it all.
That's the top of the line.
That's it.
SANTANA: Sincere, honest, true,
for real, and genuine.
Those five things.
If you have those five things,
then you can play the blues.
Otherwise, you're going to sound
like a parakeet
repeating something
that you don't understand.
BONO: He's great in every way.
Just the girth of the man
is great.
♪♪
WILLIS: He's played
probably in every country
where they have electricity,
and probably a couple
where they don't.
MAYER: B.B. King is gone
when he's playing.
B.B. King's been gone
in the world of the blues,
just living in that ether
for so long
that he belongs to it.
♪♪
[ Rhythmic clapping ]
KING: Hey!
[ Finale plays ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
[ Whistling ]
Thank you very much.
To be here
where somebody can truly say,
"B, this is where you were born.
This is where the world first
knew about you, right here,"
is a high for me,
'cause I feel very good.
My mother was named Nora Ella.
My father was named Albert Lee.
But for a young couple that
hadn't been married too long
and their first kid coming out,
they lived not too far
back over here.
And I believe my mother loved me
and I loved her,
and everything she tried
to teach me, I tried to learn.
My mom left and moved
to Kilmichael, Mississippi.
I noticed that my mother had big
spots of blood clots in her eye.
She died of diabetes
the same as her son have,
this one.
I had been living with
other people all of my life
since my mom.
Their roots,
as they sometimes say,
I think my beginning
was Elkhorn School.
At that time,
I had to walk about
five miles a day to school.
MATTHEWS: Four months' school
did not provide much education
on a plantation.
He said, "I'm a big boy.
I ought to be in the field,
not in school."
KING: I was a regular hand
from the time I was 7 years old.
See, they used to didn't have
no child labor laws
and all that.
So I was doing farm work
just like the adults was
was when I was 7.
I started about what
we call from "can to can't."
"Can" means when you can see,
"can't" when you cannot see.
♪ Ooh, Lord,
ain't my troubles so hard ♪
my troubles so hard ♪
MATTHEWS: Out of that condition,
the blues were born.
KING: Usually one guy
would be plowing by himself,
or maybe one guy
would take his hoe
and chop way out
in front of everybody else.
And usually,
you would hear this guy sing.
♪♪
♪ Oh, I wake up in the morning ♪
BLAND: That's the only time
you'd get a chance
to sing the blues
is out in the field
because your parents didn't
allow that in the house.
Nothing but spirituals.
So if you're picking cotton,
you can sing whatever
you want to sing, you know?
FREEMAN: To play that music
and not invoke the name
of Jesus or God, I guess,
then who are you invoking?
The Devil.
TROUT: A lot of people
in the church,
they go through this thing
that it's the Devil's music,
but the way he plays
and the way he sings,
that is a gift from God.
And if you are at all religious,
you will believe
that he has that gift
and that he was touched when
he was, you know, in the womb.
FAIR: When he joined the church,
well, Archie was a preacher.
My brother-in-law
was a preacher.
He preached his church out.
KING: Reverend Archie Fair
was our pastor
and the first person I ever
heard play electric guitar,
and that's why
I wanted to be like him.
FAIR: In the church,
this boy would get a chance
to play on Archie's guitar
a little.
KING: This preacher,
after church
on a Sunday afternoon,
would visit his sister,
which was my aunt.
And he'd always lay this guitar
on the bed,
and I'd go get it as soon
as they turned their backs.
So I think this is
really what started me
to fooling with the guitar,
not by listening
to some of the other people.
He was a preacher and a teacher,
and I liked him, worshiped him.
♪♪
When my grandmother died,
I still stayed
in the little house
that my grandmother and I
had lived in before she died.
I felt deserted.
Nobody but me.
And I remember
she owed something like $35,
$40 or something,
but we didn't make much money.
I was making $15 a month, so...
But I paid
my grandmother's bill.
I paid it off myself.
After my daddy got me
and brought me
to Lexington, Mississippi,
and I started going
to school there,
which was the first big school
I'd ever gone to.
He had three girls and a boy,
and those was my sisters
and brother.
My daddy never told me
he loved me.
Never did.
But anytime he was very pleased,
I had that feeling.
He called me "Jack"
out of the clear blue sky.
"Jack, what do you think
about this?"
Or "What do you think
about that?"
And I'd feel so good
till I'd almost cry,
'cause I knew what that meant.
MATTHEWS: In those days,
it was oppression,
and you'd be depressed
by the oppression
because you had no rights.
Black folk had no rights.
You were not black then.
You were Negroes or niggers.
♪♪
KING: ♪ But to know me ♪
And for you that don't know it,
this citizen council,
White Citizens' Council,
began in Indianola,
Mississippi --
my home.
HENSON: Our place was to work
hard and obey the white man.
KING:
That was one of my first days
of really experiencing what
segregation was really like.
A mob had killed a boy.
They'd hung him.
It had to do with a white lady,
you know.
They had castrated him
and drug him behind a car
to the courthouse in Lexington,
Mississippi -- Lexington.
And I saw it.
And that's something
I've never forgotten, I guess,
It's something like seeing
people killed in the war.
You don't forget it.
MATTHEWS: You were just a thing,
not a human being,
just a work thing.
They had a slogan,
"If a mule die,
buy another one."
KING: "Kill a nigger,
hire another one,"
and that's the way
I was brought up.
MATTHEWS: And that meant
you were nobody.
You just about equal to a mule.
It was badder than bad.
EVERS: We all were subject
to racism and bigotry
and hatred and denial.
None of us could
get a drink of water
at a public water fountain.
So yes, he faced the same thing
that all of us faced.
There was racism, bigotry,
and hatred.
But let me add this, though.
Let me say this to you
about B.B.
He never let that turn him
against white people.
FREEMAN: Young Riley King
started dreaming of life
back in the Delta.
The Delta was home.
So late in 1941,
16-year-old Riley
jumped on his bicycle
and began to pedal his way home,
back to where
his heart belonged.
♪♪
KING: I came
to the Barrett Plantation.
So what he did --
he hired a black overseer
named Mr. Baggett,
Booker Baggett.
And we worked like crazy
because we wanted to keep him.
And Mr. Baggett is the one that
taught me to drive tractors.
Then is the time that I decided
I wanted to get married,
and I got married
to a young lady.
DAVIS: To Martha King.
In that year,
we lived in a house together.
We lived in a three-room
shotgun house.
Two doors, one in front
and one in back.
KING: Saturdays was my day.
Go to town on Saturdays
and have a good time.
CLAY: People were in and out,
gambling and doing what little
dancing they were doing.
If you didn't get
on Church Street,
you wouldn't be in Indianola.
KING: I came in in a hurry
on my way to go to a church
to sing that night.
I'd been plowing,
plowing, plowing,
and then it happened.
We got off that evening.
I cut this ignition off
of the tractor,
and I jumped down and start
running to get ready to go out,
and it started up again.
And when the tractor
started up again,
it went forward,
and all of this broke off.
Scared me half to death.
I never did stop running,
and that's the first time
I went to Memphis.
♪ And I'm walkin' ♪
♪ Walkin' and cryin' ♪
When I came to Memphis
and started hearing
all those other guys play,
I found out I wasn't nothing.
That much.
I'm still like that today.
WHITE: ♪ Dead from your eyes ♪
FREEMAN: Once in Memphis,
B.B. King sought
and found his cousin,
the great bluesman Bukka White.
KING: Bukka was born up around
West Point, Mississippi,
and a lot of people say
he taught me to play,
but that's not true.
But he did teach me quite a bit
about being a blues player.
Bukka White used to tell me
that to be a blues singer,
you should always dress
like you was trying to go
to the bank to borrow money.
Which means you dressed,
well, a word musicians use,
kind of sharp, you know.
And he used to play
with a slide on his finger.
And I could never get that.
I've got stupid fingers.
They just wouldn't work.
So in order to get somewhat
the type sound that he had,
I would trill my hand,
like that.
And I think over the years,
I've done pretty good with it.
I still don't have it right.
I stayed up there
for about six to eight months,
and then I called some of family
back and I said,
"Tell Mr. Barrett I'm sorry.
And I would like to work
and pay it off."
Well, with wobbly legs,
I came back,
and I think
it cost me $500 or $600,
and I paid it off.
And the next time I left to go
to Memphis to start my career,
I started it correctly.
♪ Whoa, Lord ♪
♪ What a beautiful city ♪
♪ Oh, what a beautiful city ♪
♪♪
When we left Mississippi
going to Memphis,
we expected many, many things
to happen, and it did.
The late Sonny Boy,
the second Sonny Boy Williamson,
he was on the radio
in West Memphis, Arkansas.
I decided I wanted to go
and see him one day,
and one day I did.
And when I went over to see him,
I begged him
to let me sing a song
So he made me audition,
and I did,
and he liked it,
and he put me
on the show that day.
And that night,
he had two jobs to play.
One of them he didn't want
because it didn't pay
much money.
So he called the lady
and asked the lady that
he was supposed to play for,
did she hear the program?
She said yes.
So I went over there, man,
and they paid me $12 --
12 American dollars.
That's a lot of bread, you know,
for a guy that had been making
like 35 cents a hundred
picking cotton, you know?
She said, "If you can get a job
on the radio,
like Sonny Boy has,
I'll give you this job,
and you can play
six nights a week."
And I thought about that
and said,
"God, I hope I can get me
in a job on the radio."
♪♪
Well, I'm just a blues singer,
a tractor driver,
a truck driver.
I was a disc jockey for a while.
I sing the blues
because I lived it.
You're probably wondering,
"That guy,
the way you talk,
you're a disc jockey?"
Trust me.
I was for about five years.
This is B.B. King making
a statement and a natural fact.
WDIA.
Everybody want to know
why I sing the blues.
The first all-black operated
station in the Mid South,
in fact, I think in the nation.
[ Radio tuning ]
THOMAS: It's a good,
good morning to you
on an all-blues Saturday
here on WDIA
with your Rufus Thomas.
KING: This new radio station
was being opened in Memphis,
so when the red light
went off the air
I went to the window
and I knocked.
So he came to the door and said,
"What can I do for you,
young fella?"
And I said, 'Well,
I want to make a record
and I want to go on the radio,'"
and he laughed.
And Mr. Ferguson said,
"Well, we don't make records,"
and then he had
this deep look --
thought look on his face.
And he said to Mr. Williams,
he said,
"You know, we've got
this new product."
He said, "Maybe he would be good
for this new product."
So he went and got me a bottle,
and he held it up like this.
He said, "This is Pep-Ti-Kon.
Do you think you could write
a jingle for it?"
I started to thinking about it,
and I said, "Yes, sir,
I can write a jingle."
So it went like this.
♪ Pep-Ti-Kon sure is good ♪
♪ You can get it anywhere
in your neighborhood ♪
He said, "You're hired."
[ Laughs ]
♪♪
MAN: Blues Boy King.
Blues Boy, who --
Did your dad name you that?
KING: No, I used to be
a disc jockey in Memphis,
and they called me the Boy from
Beale Street, the Blues Boy.
So people,
instead of saying Blues Boy,
they just started using
the word "B.B.,"
which meant Blues Boy.
And my real name is
Riley B. King.
Now most times if someone would
come up and say, "Hi, Riley,"
I would wonder
who they're taking about.
LOCKWOOD:
I taught him the best I could.
A lot of times
he didn't understand
what I was telling him,
But when I put him with a group
that put pressure on him
and he had to learn.
You can't work with nobody
without you knowing.
You see where the bass player is
right now
when you see B.B. playing?
The bass player's
right behind him.
That's what he listens to.
Now you know.
KING: In fact, it's like --
I usually tell the band
like I have today --
"You know a lot more than I do
and you play better than I do,
but I'm the band leader."
LOCKWOOD.: B.B. was
just learning how to play,
but he always could sing
and he finally learned
how to play.
RAITT: You can look
at B.B. King's life
and listen to his music
from the beginning until the end
and in one career
and one man's contribution,
you can really have
the whole ball of wax
of what's important
and what will endure,
because there's no records
more seminal
than B.B. King's
important contribution
as a guitar player
and as a singer
and those records have
always stood the test of time.
♪♪
MAN: I've always wanted
to meet Helen.
KING: Helen? Who's Helen?
MAN: Helen, Helen,
uh, your guitar, you know.
When you start playing --
KING: Oh, you're talking about
Lucille?
This is Lucille.
That's my baby.
[ Laughter ]
MAN: That's not the guitar I saw
you with last night, B.B.
[ Laughter ]
KING: The first one
that was named Lucille
was because of a fight
in a little night club.
So, this particular night,
two guys started to fight
and one of them knocked the
other one over on this container
and the fuel
spilled on the floor
and it was already burning,
so they tried to put it out.
It seemed to burn more.
Everybody in the little club
that was dancing
started to run outside,
including me.
But when I got on the outside,
I remembered that I had ran off
and left my guitar.
So I started back for it
and the fellas there
that were working with me said,
"No, don't to it."
But I went anyway.
And I got my guitar,
but I was almost burned to death
trying to save it.
So the next morning,
we found that two men
had gotten burned,
got trapped in the building,
got burned to death.
And we also found that these two
guys was fighting about a lady.
The lady's name was Lucille.
I named the guitar Lucille
to remind me not to do
a thing like that again,
and I haven't.
[ Laughs ]
♪ Now, darling ♪
♪ You know I love you ♪
FREEMAN: Beale Street
entrepreneur Robert Henry
started to look after
the interests of B.B. King.
This resulted in a national tour
of the main black theaters
and clubs,
known as the Chitlin' Circuit.
The road was no place
for a marriage.
The road
was B.B. King's new home.
DAVIS: And he called me and
said, "'Cile," I said, "Yes?"
He said "Martha's done left me."
I said, "Girl, why you leaving?"
And she said,
"'Cause he won't stay at home.
He playing -- going everywhere."
I said, "Girl, you crazy.
You should stay
with your husband."
But she didn't.
OWENS: This business
is a very difficult business,
but I couldn't live without it
and I don't think he could
live without it, either.
♪ Oh, gone and left me, baby ♪
♪ For someone else ♪
KING: A little bit later on,
after I had been touring
for a while,
then I turned the disc jockey
loose and just toured.
And I'm still doing that.
♪♪
P. WALKER: At the time when B.B.
got his first bus,
there was excitement
because coming out
of a station wagon
into a big
Continental Trailway bus
was just a marvelous feat
for the group.
And it was something
that none of the other groups
had, either.
WITHERS:
This is the original picture
of the B.B. King Band
on Beale Street in 1955.
C. WALKER: I think
everybody knows this band
as the B.B. King Band.
This the B.B. King Band.
No matter how many bands
he goes through,
this will always be
the B.B. King Band.
OWENS: We were bad.
[ Laughter ]
Yeah, we were good.
On the seat,
you would have a box of food
like pork and beans
and sardines and crackers
and that kind of stuff,
because a lot of times
you wouldn't have time
to eat at a restaurant
or café, per se.
And it was very difficult
because a lot of the places
you couldn't go in anyway.
MARTIN LUTHER KING JR.:
And I've seen the Promised Land.
I may not get there with you,
but I want you to know tonight
that we, as a people,
will get to the Promised Land.
WITHERS:
Desegregation of America
didn't start until the '60s,
and B.B. had been on a roll
for a good 10, 12 years
before that.
OWENS:
We just played everywhere --
Apollo Theater
to the honky-tonk joints,
all over the country.
GUY:
Well, B was always on the road.
He's the only guy, I think --
I think he had a record
that he plays 365 days one year.
And I'd tell him all the time,
"I don't want that record."
He can keep that one.
You know?
DR. JOHN: I used to work
like 320 days a year.
B.B. worked more gigs.
OWENS: I don't know where
he gets the energy from.
I mean, this man
works more than anybody
because the road is his home.
♪♪
KING EVANS: No night off.
365 days a year.
Some days we didn't even get
a chance to go to sleep.
♪ I've got
a sweet little angel ♪
♪ I love the way
she spreads her wings ♪
KING EVANS: He told me
he wasn't going to ask my mom
to get married
because he felt
that she would say no,
and he didn't want that.
So he said, "We'll just have to
wait until you get 18."
So I said, "Okay,"
and that's what we did.
And he was in Detroit
at the time.
Actually, I was 18 in March,
but he wanted to put off
getting married until June
when we were in Detroit
because he wanted
Reverend Franklin,
who was Aretha Franklin's
father, to marry us.
So we waited
until we got to Detroit,
got the license,
and Reverend Franklin
married us.
♪♪
BONO: All I know is
he he'd be a hard man
to have a relationship with
because he's moving so fast.
I mean, the dude sits down
when he's playing,
but he is running
through the year.
KING EVANS:
After we got married,
we got in the car,
went to Cleveland,
he went to work,
and we just
kept going after that.
Just one day led into another.
♪ Please tell me
the reason why ♪
♪♪
RODGERS: One of the things
that B.B. has
is a great rapport
with the audience, you know,
I mean, he did that song --
♪ I bought you
a brand-new Ford ♪
♪ And you wanted a Cadillac ♪
♪ I bought you a $10 dinner ♪
♪ You said,
"Thanks for the snack" ♪
♪ I let you stay
in my penthouse ♪
♪ and you said
it was just a shack. ♪
♪ I gave you seven children ♪
♪ And now you want to
give 'em back ♪
give them back ♪
♪ Yes, I've been
down-hearted, baby ♪
SANTANA: If you want to hear
B.B. King,
the crème de la crème,
like Dexter Gordon would say,
"Listen to
"Live at the Regal,"
and every note, every word,
every song,
everything is a perfect,
flawless diamond.
TROUT: All of us in this genre
or all of us
in any kind of roots music,
we take what came before us.
KING: One of my favorites,
real favorites,
was Django Reinhardt.
♪♪
TRUCKS: The last
two or three generations
are all students of B.B.
Everybody from B.B.'s generation
are all students of T-Bone.
I mean, he really was the guy,
you know?
KING: Well just before I went in
the Army, about '42, I think,
I heard of a guy called
T-Bone Walker.
T-BONE WALKER:
♪ I'm in love with a woman ♪
♪ But she's not
in love with me ♪
KING: And I imagine today
if you listen to my playing,
you'll hear a little bit
of all of them.
I'm telling my secrets.
But I think a little bit
of all of those people I liked,
with my own ideas,
created the B.B. King
twangy guitar sound, maybe.
♪♪
KING EVANS: It's tough
because usually divorces come
because of cheating
or you fall out of love
or you have money problems,
and we had all those things
and we survived them,
but the love always stayed.
KING: If you're going to be
a traveling musician,
marriage should be something
you wouldn't want to do
until you're not traveling
a lot,
because there's very few
travelling musicians that I know
that have been able
and successful in marriage life.
KING EVANS: It's very difficult
to have a family life
with someone who's working
on the road 365 days a year.
KING: 'Cause the nice thing is
when you are married.
The terrible thing
when you're being divorced.
It's awful.
♪♪
♪ Got to go to work
this morning ♪
♪ Seems like
everything is lost ♪
♪ I got a cold-hearted... ♪
SEIDENBERG: He came to me,
I didn't come to him.
MAN: Right.
SEIDENBERG:
And he was brought to me
because he had financial
problems -- big time.
KING: Sid helped me out.
He helped me get out of trouble
with the government
and a few other things.
So I said, "Well, look,
you're my CPA,
but you've been doing everything
that my manager should do.
Well, why don't you be
my manager?"
In fact, I asked him.
He didn't ask me.
WINTERS: Well, I was 17
at a little club in Beaumont
called The Raven.
I had a fake I.D. and got in.
KING: We were playing,
and I saw these four
white people come in,
and one was extra white.
Jonny Winters.
WINTERS: We were the only
white people in the club,
and he'd been having
tax problems,
and he thought we were
from the IRS
come to bust him for his taxes.
KING: So I was so shocked
and surprised
that it wasn't about the IRS,
it took me a little while
to kind of get my feet
back on the ground, you know?
WINTERS: He kept saying,
"Well, we have arrangements."
And I was like,
"I've heard all your records.
I know all your arrangements."
He asked to see my union card.
He really checked me out.
KING: I let him sit in,
and he was good.
I'll tell you.
He was good.
WINTERS:
It's just that he's a saint.
He's a blues saint.
CRAY: The first chance to play
in front of a white audience
it's like,
"Who are these people?"
KING: I'm grateful that
some of them seemed to like me.
I'm grateful because to me,
it seemed to open
a few doors for us
that seemed like they was
never going to be opened.
So I sent my road manager
and told them to go
and tell Bill I was there,
but I thought
it was the wrong place,
so we were going to leave.
So Bill came back out
with the road manager
and came on the bus.
He said, "No,
you're at the right place."
SANTANA: I happened to be there.
The opening act was Otis Rush
and Steve Miller and B.B. King.
KING: And he said,
"Ladies and gentlemen,"
and would you believe that
when he said that,
you could hear a pin drop.
He said, "I bring you
the Chairman of the Board,
B.B. King."
I've never been introduced
like that before or since.
When he mentioned my name,
they all stood up.
And I was so touched till
I cried standing up there.
SANTANA: It was like watching
a chandelier.
All I could see was his tears
and the diamond ring
that he had --
to wipe his tears.
And I was still washing dishes
at the time.
I was living with my mom.
And when I saw B.B. receive
that kind of adulation,
that kind of honor,
I said, "This is what I want."
KING: So I felt weird.
It felt real weird.
But I did it.
And after that,
I cried back up the stairway.
SEIDENBERG: It's like when
Nat King Cole broke through
and they accepted him,
so we kept doing that
after the initial '68 period,
working The Fillmore,
working colleges.
And then all of a sudden,
we were able to book B.B.
into these rock 'n' roll clubs
and other venues that never had
black entertainers before.
DR. JOHN: And it shifted
a couple of gears there,
right there,
and B.B. could do whatever
the hell he wanted to do.
KING:
♪ The thrill has gone away ♪
♪ You know you done me wrong,
baby ♪
♪ And you're gonna be sorry
someday ♪
SZYMCZYK: I figured if I could
take some different players
and put them around B.B.
that something good
would happen.
Very shortly after that,
it was only like
eight months later,
we were scheduled to do
another album and I said,
"I'd like to do it all
with them, B."
He said, "Sure,
let's do it all that way."
And the big success that
resulted out of the second album
was "The Thrill is Gone."
♪♪
KING:
♪ The thrill is gone ♪
♪ The thrill is gone away ♪
STARR: John actually brought in
"The Thrill Is Gone"
and played it to all of us.
I have that great memory
of that.
♪♪
BIHARI: B.B. had really
a million-selling record then,
and that really put B.B. King
into a different category
completely.
♪♪
♪ I am the little red rooster ♪
♪ Too lazy to crow for day ♪
FRANCE: Sid was a big proponent
of exposing B.B.
to other audiences,
so sometimes he took dates
that were not as lucrative
financially.
♪ Too lazy to crow for day ♪
WYMAN: We never saw B.B.
or had anything to do with B.B.
until '69
when we took him on tour.
♪ Hounds begin to howl ♪
He'd take the band
right down to a whisper,
and it was amazing.
You'd just hear the ting-ting
with the little guitar lines,
and then he'd build and build
and build
into this massive sort of sound
with the band.
♪♪
[ Applause ]
KING: Ha!
Thank you!
The many people
that I hadn't played to
or hadn't heard of me
started to, I think,
listen to me
and pay attention to me
from that tour.
♪♪
♪ If you see
my little red rooster ♪
TAYLOR: They themselves would be
the first ones to admit
that they started out
as a blues band.
They were always very good
at paying homage
to the blues artists
that influenced them.
JAGGER: We went to record
at the legendary Chess Studios,
which was on
South Michigan Avenue.
RICHARDS: Yeah,
they wanted to know, like,
how we were doing it
and why we wanted to do it.
You know?
"Why you want to play like me?"
Well, it happens to be
very good stuff.
[ Laughs ]
You know?
And one day I might get there.
JAGGER: They were very,
very generous to us,
and they passed on all the tips
and gave us all the help
and they were very, very kind.
And I want to salute those guys.
Most of them
are not with us anymore.
Of course, one is,
B.B. King, who I --
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
SZYMCZYK: The only tune
I ever brought in
that I asked B.B. to do,
and that was "Hummingbird,"
the Leon Russell song,
and to get Leon
to come and play with B.B.
You know, getting people
to come play with B.B.
was never a problem.
WALSH: I played on a song
called "Hummingbird"
that Leon Russell wrote.
RUSSELL: He plays
those little obbligatos --
when he sings
and he plays a lick,
then he sings
and he plays another lick.
It turns out he does that
when he talks, too.
So he was talking to me and,
"One time I was down
in Tuscaloosa..."
♪ Da, da, dum ♪
And I listened to it
a couple times,
and then I started playing
the background to it.
And they're not all the same.
They're not in the same keys.
They're not the same groove
or anything.
And so he had finished it.
We'd finished the song,
what key, whatever it was,
we played the ending.
He didn't say anything,
And he'd start talking about
something else,
and he'd play something else
and I'd play that background.
We got into about the third one,
and B.B. started crying.
He said,
"I've never had that before."
So that's very touching to me.
I was such a student of his.
I knew what he meant when he
said those things on the guitar,
so it was
the greatest compliment.
♪♪
FREEMAN: In 1971,
B.B. King flew the nest
and ventured
on his first overseas tour.
This cumulated
in a collaborative album
called "B.B. King in London."
♪ And I love her just the same ♪
KING:
No, just accent with the break
Okay, we're starting again
from the top
so you get a feel
of what I'm talking about.
Not the top --
the top of the last one.
Okay?
♪ Fast movin' baby ♪
♪ I can't do nothing
to slow you down ♪
♪ Your speed is supersonic,
mama ♪
♪ And you're faster than sound ♪
♪ No, no ♪
STARR: When B.B. came to London
to make that album,
"B.B. in London,"
I was invited to play.
It was just incredible.
We're playing away,
and B.B. sort of looks at me.
And I thought, "Oh, he wants to
end the song," so I --
Ba-da-bum-ba-be-dub bum.
And he goes, "Too good to lose,"
and we came right in again,
It was like, "Oh, my God!"
It was so great.
We just kicked it in again.
And he did pay me a huge
compliment in those sessions
because he called me.
"Hey, Ringo,
you were just like a clock --
tick-tock, tick-tock."
TEDESCHI:
He just had everything --
everything that you'd want
out of a performer, you know?
He had the energy,
the charisma, you know?
He's handsome.
He's got beautiful tone.
Everything had a meaning,
Every note just like a punch,
you know?
[ Cheers and applause ]
LEVINE: In 1974,
I produced a big event.
I stepped out of my usual life
and produced this big event
in Zaire in 1974
that surrounded the fight
between George Foreman
and Muhammad Ali.
And I brought B.B. over.
A few years later,
I got a call from B.B.
saying that he really needed
to make a record
and would I be interested?
♪♪
We made our first record
with B.B.
The magic of recording
is the danger in recording.
When someone's played something
for three years
and they come up and walk
into a studio and play it,
they know it.
They've been through it
so many times.
But when they're engaging it
for the first time
and if can capture that moment,
you've got yourself
something special.
KING: ♪ Oh, you know ♪
♪ I'm having so much trouble,
people ♪
♪ Baby, I wonder,
yes, I wonder ♪
♪ Baby, I wonder ♪
♪ Oh, I wonder what in the
world's gonna happen to me ♪
♪♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
Thank you!
FREEMAN: Many people tend
to slow down in their 60s.
Not B.B. King.
His next collaboration with
a young band from Ireland
was about to propel B.B.
to a whole new audience.
MAN: Well, you tour
with The Rolling Stones
and then you go with
the popular group of now,
and that's with Bono and U2.
Huh?
KING: [ Laughs ]
My number one.
[ Where the Streets
Have No Name" plays ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
BONO: Keith Richards played
blues records to us,
and I began this kind of journey
to discover who were the greats.
And B.B. King's not just,
you know, great,
He's like great.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Believe it or not, B.B. King
came to Dublin, Ireland,
and he was playing in this club
in Dublin, Ireland,
and we wrote this song for him.
This is called
"When Love Comes to Town."
I gave it my absolute,
you know, everything I had
in that howl
at the start of the song,
and then B.B. King
opened up his mouth
and I felt like a girl.
♪ Now I stand accused
of the things I've said ♪
BOTH: ♪ When love comes to town
I'm gonna jump that train ♪
♪ When love comes to town
I'm gonna catch that flame ♪
♪ Maybe I was wrong
to ever let you down ♪
♪ But I did what I did
before love came to town ♪
♪♪
BONO: We had learnt.
We'd absorbed.
But the more we tried
to be like B.B.,
the less convincing we were.
KING: I'm no good with chords,
so what we do is
get somebody else
to play chords.
BONO: Sure.
Well, Edge will do that.
There's not much chords
in this song.
I think there's only two.
KING: I'm horrible with chords.
♪♪
BONO: When we were working on
"When Love Comes to Town,"
we were sitting around
and we were showing him
the chords.
And he said, "Gentlemen...
gentlemen...
I don't do chords.
I do this."
KING: I don't know
what to do there.
I'm just gonna --
BONO: Just go ahead, yeah.
Is that a joke?
[ Laughs ]
♪♪
But there was this great sense
of camaraderie in his band
and it was a joy, just a joy
to share a stage with B.B. King,
that rich, brassy sound
they had behind them
with the horn section and --
And then his grace, you know?
He's a lesson in grace.
The debt is very much
in his direction.
♪♪
CLAPTON: The character
of any great musician
is usually identifiable
by the individuality
of their vibrato.
♪♪
Most players are recognizable
by that particular facet
of their playing,
and that's how I would know
B.B.'s playing.
Hit one note --
I can tell B.B. from one note.
You know, most of us can,
I think.
TAYLOR:
I'd say that's true, yeah.
I mean, his sound
is completely unique to him.
MAYALL:
If you can just play one note
and somebody else can say --
recognize who that is.
BLAND: One note,
you know that's him and Lucille.
WILLIS: He can take one note
and make it so sexy.
CLAPTON: One note, you know,
is all it takes.
BONAMASSA:
The note with the vibrato.
-CRAY: One note.
-TRUCKS: One note.
LANG: In one note.
♪♪
SANTANA: That note is not
in the amplifier and it's not --
It's not even at his fingers.
It's coming from the center
of his heart.
You know, I can hear B.B. King
with the sound off on the TV,
just by looking at his face.
♪♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
GUY: I remember Eric Clapton
was on CNN,
and they asked him who he had
never played with.
And B.B. evidentially
was watching it
because I was,
and he said, "B.B. King."
CLAPTON:
The first time I met him,
I sat and played with him.
There are pictures of me and him
sitting on amplifiers.
It was a long time ago.
It's '66, '67.
♪♪
BOTH:
♪ I dreamed I had a good job ♪
KING: The CD he did with me
called "Riding with the King,"
he named it, I didn't.
He had the ideas,
most of the ideas for it.
CLAPTON: "Next year,
don't do anything during
that period and we'll do it."
And he stuck to it, you know.
It was a commitment
we both kept.
KING: "Whatever you think
is good, we'll try it."
And we did.
CLAPTON: So I thought best thing
to do is I'll just --
We'll just go into the room with
a couple of acoustic guitars
and see what comes out.
KING: And they were good.
Everything.
Except trying to make me play
acoustic guitar.
I didn't like that.
[ Laughs ]
CLAPTON: [ Laughs ]
BOTH: ♪ Don't you know
you're riding with the King? ♪
♪♪
FREEMAN: In 2008,
Indianola showed its gratitude
and opened the B.B. King Museum.
Every year, tens of thousands
of people visit
from all over the world
to this little town
in Mississippi
to share one of the greatest
journeys ever told.
BONO: You know, the only person
who doesn't think B.B.'s great
is probably B.B.
♪♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
KING: Thank you so much.
Thank you.
[ Cheers and applause
intensify ]
People call me
King of the Blues.
I've heard it many, many times.
Do you think I think that?
No, I do not.
I think there's a lot of people
that can do exactly what I do
and a lot of them
can do it better.
They're just not me.
♪ Did you ever hear
a church bell tone? ♪
♪ Ever hear
a church bell tone?
♪ Did you ever hear
a church bell tone? ♪
♪ Then you know that old B
is dead and gone ♪
L. TONEY:
He never forgets old friends.
If he's aware
of a situation with one,
or an old band member who --
He considers them all family,
current and past.
JAMES: He cares about people.
He loves people.
LOCKWOOD: And I think he was
the most easygoing person
I ever seen.
NEVILLE: He wanted to share
his talent and his soul
with the world,
and that's what he did.
DR. JOHN: He's a one of a kind.
RAITT:
I mean, he's just like --
You know? Unbelievable.
WYMAN: There's only one B.B.
BONO: For true greatness
to take place,
there requires a long obedience
in the same direction.
KING: I can't tell anybody
what I want to hear,
but I have a --
I hear it myself,
but I can't play it.
I don't know how
to really get it myself.
I think sometimes
the sound that I hear
has never been
the sound that I want to hear,
if I make sense.
It is a little sound that I hear
but I can't tell anybody
about it.
When I hear what
I would like to hear, if ever,
I think I'd have to stop
because it probably won't sound
as good as I'm thinking it will.
[ Laughs ]
RAITT: I think that
as a lesson in living,
you can look at B.B. and also
learn what it's like to be a man
and get through all those
difficult times he had
and come through with the heart
that he still has.
That's no mean accomplishment.
KING: I don't think I've done
the best that I could have done.
I thought I had.
I thought that I did everything
the best I could,
but when I look back,
I see there are some slacks.
You can do better.
L. TONEY: I've never told him,
but I sometimes call him
the father of us all,
because that's the way
I see him.
It's very difficult
to find words to say.
[ Sniffles ]
Excuse me.
MATTHEWS: He sang the blues
and did a great job of it
and rose to a great height,
were even invited
by kings and potentates
from where he was.
KING:
I've never met a king before,
so I'm a bit nervous
but also grateful, so grateful.
POPE JOHN PAUL II:
[ Speaking Italian ]
I said, "Holy Father,
I know you're always doing
things for others,
so I want to do something
for you, Sir," I said.
"I'd like to offer
my guitar to you."
He took it himself.
He stepped
and took it from the guy,
and he smiled again.
Then he said, "Happy holidays
to you and your family, B.B."
Oh, my God!
He said "B.B."
♪ Lead me on, Lord ♪
♪ To the light ♪
♪ Take my hand ♪
♪ Precious Lord ♪
♪ Lead me home ♪
PRESIDENT OBAMA:
You know, some nights
when you want to go out and just
take a walk, clear your head,
or jump into a car
just to take a drive,
you can't do it.
Secret Service won't let you,
and that's frustrating.
But then there are other nights
where B.B. King and Mick Jagger
come over to your house...
[ Laughter ]
...to play for a concert.
♪♪
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Baby, don't you wanna go ♪
[ Cheering ]
KING: ♪ Same old place ♪
PRESIDENT OBAMA:
♪ Sweet home Chicago ♪
[ Cheers and applause ]
BARBOUR: Now it's my honor,
as Governor
of the state of Mississippi,
to proclaim February 15, 2005
as B.B. King Day for the entire
state of Mississippi.
And I urge all citizens
to join me and the legislature
in celebrating and honoring
this great Mississippian.
[ Applause ]
KING: I am so happy.
Thank you.
[ Cheers and applause ]
EVERS: The only thing about
the blues since B.B.'s gone,
like everything else,
the world goes on.
It's not gonna stop
because B.B. King leave,
but it will never be the same.
But I'm here to tell you
B.B. is leaving a legend
that's gonna be hard to be beat.
P. WALKER: [ Crying ] We just
got a B.B. King in our life.
And there ain't nothing else
like him.
KING: When I start to sound
as bad as I think I will
when I get a certain age...
[ Laughs ]
I hope that it, you know, that a
little bell will ring in my head
that says "Time to stop."
But other than that,
I'll wait till the great one
upstairs takes me away.
FREEMAN:
What makes somebody great,
somebody special?
When you look at a man's life,
can you truly say
that man made a difference?
People say
folk are born that way
or were blessed
by a higher force.
KING:
Play the best that I can,
reach as many people as I can,
as many countries --
In other words,
I'd like the whole world
to be able to hear B.B. King
sing and play the blues.
♪ I swear by stars above ♪
♪ I'll keep my word, my love ♪
Funding for "American Masters"
is provided by...
Support for this program
also provided by...
...and by contributions
to your PBS station
from viewers like you.
♪♪
-♪ You're sitting there
looking proud ♪
♪ And thinking you're so fine ♪
♪ You're trying to run around ♪
♪ With each and every friend
of mine ♪
♪ You're thinking
you're so smart, baby ♪
♪ And think that I'm a fool ♪
♪ But baby, let me tell you,
you'd better play it cool ♪
♪ You'll never miss
your wallet, baby... ♪
-To learn more about B.B. King
and other American masters,
visit PBS.org/americanmasters,
or find us on Facebook, Twitter,
and Tumblr.
"B.B. King: The Life of Riley"
is available on Blu-Ray and DVD.
To order, visit shopPBS.org
or call 1-800-PLAY-PBS.
♪♪
♪ ♪
You're Watching PBS.
GATES: I'M HENRY
LOUIS GATES, JR.
WELCOME TO
FINDING YOUR ROOTS.