THE FOOT ON THE VERY SAME BEACH.
WELL, THANKS SO MUCH TO YOU FOR
JOINING US TODAY.
I'M JIM SCIUTTO.
FOLLOW ME ON
TWITTER @JIMSCIUTTO.
"AT THIS ó=HOUR" WITH KATE BOULN
STARTS RIGHT NOW.0@
■%■■v-v■p■■C@
Ñ) HELLO, EVERYONE.■■■■W■W■■ANK.
A■■■7■■w■■B.■7w■We■W■W■W■■w
INVESTIGATORS WARN■e■■ A■F■
■F BORDER FACILITIES.■W■7■F■F■FW
A GOVERNMENT REPORT,■■■■■uu■■F■
ADVOCACY GROUP, NOT DEMOCRATIC
MEMB ■W■W■■e■■771
NOT RNEYS REPRESENTING MIGRANT.
THIS IS A 16-PAGE REPORT
COMPILED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF
HOMELAND SECURITY.
LOOK AT THESE;p IMAGES.
OUND■ á  SHOCK
MASS OVERCROWDI OF CHILDREN
SOME WITH NO■@ SHOWERSN CLOTHE.
SOME CHILDREN WITH N ACCESS TO
WARM MEALS FOR DAYS.
ADULTS FORCED INTO STANDING ROOM
ONLY CONDITIONS FOR A WEHE
REPORT SAYS.
OFFICIALS DESCRIBE THE MIGRANTS
EVEN AS BANGING ON CELL WINDOWS
AND HOLDING UPOR HELP.
AND TH ARE
I
THESE AR>ñññññ■ IMAGES DRAWN BY
CHILDREN WHO RECENTLY WERE
RELEASED FROM BORDER FACILITIES.
THE DRAWINGS APPEAR TO SHOW
CHILDREN -- YOU KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOUR EYES TELL YOU.
IN CAGES, IN JAIL.
THE AMERICAN ACADEMY OF
PEDIATRICS RELEASED THESE
, SAYING THESE
FACILITIES, IN THEIR WORDS, ARE
NO PLACE FOR C■■'S A PAINFó REM
THESE CHILDREN ARE GOING THROU
AND ARE GOING THROUGH NOW.
LE STRAIGHT OVER TO CNN'S
NICK VALEN BORDER
FACILITY IN EL PASO, TEXAS.
NICK, WHAT'S THE LATEST?
>> Reporter: WELL, IT'S A BIT OF
BREAKING NEWS THIS MORNING.
WE'RE HEARING FROM ACTING DHS
SECRETARY ABOUT THOSE SOCIAL
MEDIA POSTS.
REMEMBER EARLIER THIS WEEK,
KATE, WE REPORTED ABOUT THIS
CLOSED FACEBOOK GROUP THAT
FEATURED CURRENT AND FORMER,
THEY SAY, BORDER PATROL AGENTS
MAKING LEWD COMMENTS, DEROGATORY
COMMENTS, RACIALLY INFLAMMATORY
COMMENTS, JOKING ABOUT DEAD
MIGRANTS.
NOW THE ACTING DHS SECRETARY
TWEETING THIS, THIS MORNING.
I HAVE DIRECTED AN IMMEDIATE
INVESTIGATION AND AS THE U.S.
BORDER PATROL CHIEF HAS MADE
CLEAR, ANY EMPLOYEE FOUND TO
HAVE COMPROMISED THE PUBLIC'S
TRUST WILL BE HELD ACCOUNTABLE.
WHAT'S UNCLEAR AT THIS MOMENT,
WE WERE UNDER THE UNDERSTANDING
THAT EARLIER THIS WEEK AN
INVESTIGATION HAD ALREADY BEEN
UNDER WAY.
THE POSTS WERE SAID TO HAVE BEEN
TURNED OVER TO INTERNAL AFFAIRS
AT CBP.
THE DHS INSPECTOR GENERAL IS
ALSO SAID TO HAVE GOTTEN THEIR
HANDS ON THESE SOCIAL MEDIA
POSTS.
A BROADER QUESTION, WE'RE ALSO
WONDERING IF HE'S CALLING FOR AN
INVESTIGATION INTO THESE SOCIAL
MEDIA POSTS.
WHEN WILL HE CALL FOR AN
INVESTIGATION INTO THE
CONDITIONS IN THESE BORDER
PATROL FACILITIES?
SPEAKING ON THAT, IT WAS
YESTERDAY THAT I SPOKE TO A
LONGTIME VETERAN EL PASO BORDER
PATROL AGENT WHO SAID THEY'RE
TIRED OF SEEING THE CONDITIONS
MIGRANTS ARE BEING HELD IN AND
DECIDED TO SPEAK OUT, SO LONG AS
WE CONCEALED THEIR IDENTITY.
>> YOU'RE TAKING A BIG RISK BY
DOING THIS.
>> YES, BUT AMERICA NEEDS TO
KNOW.
THEY NEED TO KNOW THE TRUTH.
>> Reporter: A BORDER PATROL
AGENT WHO'S HAD ENOUGH.
IN A CNN EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW,
THE VETERAN AGENT WHO AGREED TO
GO ON CAMERA ONLY IF THEIR
IDENTITY WAS CONCEALED,
GROUP REPORTEDLY ATB> CLOSED
COMPRISED OF THOUSANDS OF
CURRENT AND FORMER AGENTS.
PRO PUBLICA, THE FIRST TO EXPOSE
THE GROUP, WHERE MEMBERS SHARED
LEWD AND SEXIST CONTENT ABOUT
LATINA MEMBERS OF CONGRESS,
INCLUDING ALEXANDRIA
OCASIO-CORTEZ.
THE AGENT TELLING CNN, BEING
DEROGATORY IS PART OF THE BORDER
PATROL CULTURE, EVEN HEARING A
SUPERVISOR JOKE ABOUT DEAD
MIGRANTS.
>> HE WAS MAKING FUN OF THEM.
>> SAYING WHAT?
>> THAT WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES IT
MAKE
M
MAKE, IT'S JUST ANOTHER LIFE?
HE MADE A COMMENT ALSO REGARDING
RUNNING OVER ILLEGALS.
I'M LIKE, YOU CANNOT RUN OVER
PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: IN DESCRIBING THE
CONDITIONS INSIDE THE EL PASO
DETENTION FACILITIES, THE AGENT
COMPARED THEM TO A ZOO.
>> THE HOLDING FACILITY, THE
CELLS, THEY ARE, WHAT I WILL
SAY, FILTHY.
WE HAVE A MAINTENANCE AND
CLEANING CREW THAT CLEAN THE
GENERAL AREA, LIKE THE HALLWAYS,
BUT I HAVE NEVER SEEN THEM
CLEANING COUNTERS OR CLEANING
TOILETS IN THE CELLS OR CLEANING
SINKS IN THE CELL.
SOMETIMES YOU GO IN A CELL, AND
THERE'S TRASH EVERYWHERE.
>> THERE AREHOSE IN LEADERSHIP
OF CUSTOMS AND BORDER
PROTECTION, THEY SAY THAT
MIGRANTS ARE GETTING BASIC HUMAN
RIGHTS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO LEADERS WHO
SAY THAT?
>> Reporter: WHAT IS BASIC HUMAN
RIGHTS, TOILET PAPER?
WATER FROM THE SINK?
OR IN THE SAME CLOTHING FOR
DAYS.
I REMEMBER WHEN THERE USED T
A■hCESSING CENTER.
ESPECIALLY IN WINTER, WE USED TO
HAVE THESE BLANKETS.
TEN DIFFERENT ALIENS WOULD USE
THE SAME BLANKET.
WE WOULD RECYCLE THEM.
WE'LL PUT THEM IN A BAG AND THEY
WOULDN'T GET WASHED.
>> I FEEL LIKE, YOU KNOW,
MULTIPLE TIMES DURING OUR
INTERVIEW, YOU'VE SORT OF STARED
OFF IN THE DISTANCE AND THOUGHT
ABOUT SOME THINGS YOU'VE SEEN.
IT SEEMS AS THOUGH THERE ARE
THINGS THAT YOU MIGHT TAKE HOME
WITH YOU.
>> EVERY DAY.
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> THE KIDS.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE KIDS?