have an impact
on people's lives.
-One of the most important bands
to ever walk the earth.
Their influence
will never, ever go away.
-They had the perfect
combination
with the classic lineup.
They had the personalities
that could create friction,
that created great music,
and they don't
come along very often.
-It was just a giant
firework display
that was just
the best you've ever seen,
but it wasn't built to last.
It exploded into the sky,
and we all went, "Ahh,"
and it was gone.
Fabulous.
(Siren blares)
We have a death.
We need to confirm
identification and then we
need to perform an autopsy.
The lead singer of the rock
band Nirvana, Kurt Cobain,
has died of a gunshot wound
in Seattle.
'The world was stunned
when Kurt Cobain,
the 27-year-old musician and
self-styled prince of grunge,
was found dead.'
Kurt Cobain was a genius.
He was the powerful voice
of a generation.
He was the true artist. Even
in his pain, he was genuine.
'But with success
came pressures
that Kurt found hard
to handle.'
He worked so hard to become
a millionaire rock star.
And then once he did, he
didn't like it very much.
'And on April 8th, 1994,
when Kurt Cobain was found
dead at his Seattle mansion,
it appeared to be
a clear-cut case of suicide.'
Kurt was the poster boy
for suicide.
I said, "He's going
to kill himself."
(Gunshot)
'But despite leaving
a suicide note,
many people
refused to believe
that Kurt Cobain
had taken his own life.'
I knew from the beginning
that Kurt had been murdered.
Kurt Cobain's death
certificate says that he died
from a single shotgun wound
to the head.
But why would a man who's
just achieved his lifelong
goal of becoming a rock star
and starting a family
kill himself?
Could foul play
have been involved?
'Dr. Michael Hunter is
a world-renowned forensic
pathologist
and the Chief Medical
Examiner
in one of America's
biggest cities.
He's performed
over 4,000 autopsies
to investigate and reveal
the cause of death.'
Kurt Cobain's
investigative records
show that he died from a
shotgun wound to the head,
fired through the mouth.
But why would a man who has
struggled to make it as
a musician
and who'd just started
a family, kill himself?
I'm gonna use all
the available evidence
to investigate what happened
to Kurt both mentally...
..and physically
and discover more
about why he died.
'2:30pm.
Four days before
Kurt Cobain's death.
Kurt is at the Exodus
Recovery Center
in Marina Del Rey.
He's trying to kick
the heroin addiction
he's developed since
becoming a rock star.'
One of the people he smoked
a cigarette with outside
said that Kurt just seemed
like a happy-go-lucky guy,
without a problem
in the world.
He seemed very excited
about life.
'Kurt had only recently
become a millionaire,
after a lifetime
of financial hardship,
and had just bought himself
a mansion
in an exclusive area
of Seattle,
where he lived with his wife
Courtney Love
and his 19-month-old baby,
Frances Bean.
In a recently discovered
interview,
recorded a few months
before his death,
Kurt claimed he'd never
been happier.'
Ever since I've been married
and I've had a child within
the last year,
everything - my whole mental
state and my physical state -
has almost improved
100 per cent.
I've never been
more optimistic.
But within five days of
appearing optimistic
about the future,
Kurt Cobain was dead.
He was 27
and he joins a long list of
stars who died at this age,
including Jim Morrison, Jimi
Hendrix and Amy Winehouse.
It's an exclusive club.
And I want to find out
what led Kurt to join it.
'Kurt Donald Cobain was born
on February 20th, 1967,
in Aberdeen,
a small industrial town
located two hours
south of Seattle.'
Aberdeen was a logging town
where everybody was macho.
He certainly wasn't the type
who was gonna go out
and cut down trees.
'Kurt's dad was a mechanic
and his mother
was a waitress.
But his upbringing was
far from easy.'
The whole Cobain family
was dysfunctional.
I'm talking all of us.
The dysfunctional
part, I think,
was that he was living
with parents
who were using more alcohol
than normal.
(Voices arguing)
And it's hard for you to be
a happy little kid
if you're growing up in
a family that's fighting
and who don't really know
how to raise children.
(KURT) I was ashamed
of my parents.
I couldn't face some
of my friends at school.
Because I desperately wanted
to have the classic,
typical family -
mother, father.
I wanted that security.
(Plays notes)
'Kurt's parents separated
when he was nine.
He found solace in music,
which he showed promise at
from an early age.
He was a child prodigy,
who possessed this rare,
unique artistic talent.
(BEV) Music saved Kurt.
I think it was the only way
he knew to express his
feelings.
I really do think it was
therapeutic for him.
'Kurt started
by playing the drums
before moving on to guitar.
But it wasn't until he was 18
that he met Chris Novoselic
and formed the band Nirvana.
It was Kurt's approach that
would be at the forefront
of a new style of music.
How he was able
to take punk music...
..old rock 'n' roll,
minimalist melodic music,
stick it all in a soup and
come out with what he did,
I think that was
pretty revolutionary.
'This fusion of rock and punk
became known as grunge.
It is epitomized
in their iconic track
Smells Like Teen Spirit.'
# With the lights out,
it's less dangerous
# Here we are now,
entertain us
# I feel stupid
and contagious
# Here we are now,
entertain us
# A mulatto...
'Nirvana's album Nevermind,
released in 1991,
went to the top of
the charts around the world,
and established Kurt Cobain
as the biggest rock star
of his generation.
In February 1992, Kurt
married the former stripper
and lead singer of the band
Hole, Courtney Love.'
As soon as she married him,
I listened to a lot of his
poetry and a lot of his music
and I thought, "This guy's
pretty profound."
(BEV) I think he was popular
because he was wounded.
He looked like a person
who was down on his luck
and rebellious.
So I think the kids could
really relate to that.
(IAN) He spoke to
this lost generation.
And became the voice
of the generation.
This is a photograph
of Nirvana,
taken six months prior
to Kurt Cobain's death.
And I'm surprised
at how small Kurt is.
Bass guitarist Chris
Novoselic is incredibly tall.
He's six foot six inches.
And drummer David Grohl
is six feet tall.
According to his records,
Kurt was five-nine,
but looked considerably
smaller.
This could be due to a
disorder he was suffering
from, called scoliosis.
And in this recently
discovered interview,
Kurt sheds new light
on what he thought
caused this condition.
I had scoliosis
when I was in junior high.
I've been playing guitar
ever since.
The weight of the guitar
has made my back
grow in this curvature.
So when I stand,
everything's sideways.
(DR. HUNTER) Scoliosis,
or curvature of the spine,
occurs in about
three per cent of people.
It most commonly arises
in the teenage years.
The curve is usually either
S-shaped, with two bends,
or C-shaped with one.
His music felt like
he was always in pain,
that he was angst-ridden.
That's a typical reflection
of the scoliosis
that he battled with.
It's a common misconception
that scoliosis causes pain.
But that is
not always the case.
And the cause is
oftentimes unknown.
This is an X-ray
of Kurt Cobain's spine.
It shows that he had
C-shaped scoliosis.
This wouldn't be caused by
the weight of his guitar
but it could be
exacerbated by it.
As there is no mention
of any pain
or psychological distress
associated with
this condition,
I don't believe that this was
responsible for his death.
However, Kurt did suffer
from another long-standing
medical condition
that had
a huge impact on him.
So I want to investigate
whether it led him
to take his own life.
I remember putting
on a brave face
to hide my symptoms
of depression.
I was on an antidepressant.
But I still had depression
symptoms...
It was tough getting
through the day...
hiding how I really felt.
Something had to change.
So I talked to my
doctor for real.
No more saying,
“Oh, I'm fine.”
This time, I spoke up about
living behind the mask.
And he told me about REXULTI.
He said that REXULTI, when
added to an antidepressant, ...
has been proven to help reduce
symptoms of depression.
Without giving up the progress
I may have made on
my antidepressant.
REXULTI is not for everyone.
Call your doctor about unusual
changes in behavior,
worsening depression,
or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants can increase
these in those 24 and younger.
Elderly dementia patients
taking REXULTI
have an increased risk
of death or stroke.
Call your doctor if you have
high fever, stiff muscles,
and confusion to address
a possible
life-threatening condition...
or if you have uncontrollable
muscle movements,
as these may be permanent.
REXULTI has been shown
to increase blood sugar
in some people.
Other risks are increased
cholesterol; weight gain;
unusual urges or
compulsive behaviors; ...
decreased white blood cells,
which can be serious; ...
dizziness on standing; seizures;
trouble swallowing;
and impaired judgment
or motor skills.
It was time to make a change.
That's why I asked my doctor
about adding REXULTI.
Feel better about
facing the world.
Pay $0 for your first
REXULTI prescription.
Details at REXULTI.com.
(inhale, exhale) Air Wick
You don't live in one corner.
Fragrance shouldn't either.
Air Wick's new technology
releases fragrance
upwards and outwards unlike
Febreze.
So now you can fill every corner
with fragrance.
Upgrade to Air Wick.
♪
Protect your pet
with the #1 name
in flea and tick protection.
FRONTLINE Plus.
Trusted by vets
for nearly 20 years.
This is nice.
Yeah...yeah, this is nice.
Hmm.
How did you make the dip
so rich and creamy?
Oh it's a Philadelphia--
Family recipe.
Can I see it?
No.
Philadelphia Dips. So good,
you'll take all the credit.
What makes DiGiorno Crispy Pan
Pizza different than delivery?
♪ PAN PAN PAN PAAAAN
You bake it fresh
in its own pan!
Giving our DiGiorno pizza
a crispy, caramelized crust.
♪ PAAAAN
It's not Delivery,
It's DiGiorno.
(NEWSREADER) A member of the
rock music scene is dead.
Police in Seattle say
that Kurt Cobain,
the lead singer of
the group Nirvana,
has taken his own life.
'April 8th, 1994.
Kurt Cobain is found dead
at his house in Seattle,
with a gunshot wound
to his head.
Expert coroner and forensic
pathologist Dr. Michael
Hunter
is examining all the medical
evidence available
to try and work out
if and why
Kurt Cobain
took his own life.'
Suicides are rarely down
to just one factor.
There are oftentimes
a mixture of both physical
and psychological conditions.
So I want to dig deeper,
to find out
what precipitated his death.
'The Excelsior Hotel, Rome.
One month before
Kurt Cobain's death.
Kurt has arrived in Rome to
meet his wife Courtney Love.
He's just pulled out of
Nirvana's European tour,
blaming it on bronchitis.
Kurt's relationship with
Courtney is also suffering,
with rumors of divorce.
But despite their problems,
they leave their daughter,
Frances Bean,
with their nanny
and spend the evening
drinking champagne together.'
(COURTNEY)
Do what you need to do.
(CHRISTOPHER) Champagne
is a very un-Kurtlike drink.
He wasn't really a big
drinker at the best of times.
Champagne is more of
a rock star drink.
And he wasn't into that.
'The couple drink
into the early hours
before they fall asleep.
At 6:25am, Courtney wakes
to find Kurt
is no longer beside her.'
(Clock ticks)
Kurt?
Kurt, come on, wake up.
I said, wake up!
'When she fails to wake him,
she calls for help.'
Hello? Yeah,
I need an ambulance.
(Knock at door)
'At 6:40am,
a paramedic arrives.
When he also fails
to revive Kurt,
he's taken to the
Umberto I Hospital,
less than two miles away.'
(BEV) I listened to the news.
And they said that Courtney
had found Kurt unconscious.
And blue.
Which to me means...
That's like
the color of death.
I just thought, "This guy is
a poster boy for suicide."
I went to his grandfather,
Leland,
and I told him I was really,
really worried about Kurt.
I said,
"You've got to talk to him.
He's going to kill himself."
'It was later revealed that
Kurt had left a suicide note.
He had admitted in many
interviews to using heroin,
but had in fact
overdosed on Rohypnol.'
Rohypnol is a tranquilizer,
also known as
"the date rape drug".
But it's also prescribed
to treat heroin withdrawal.
A month later, Kurt was dead,
leaving little clue if
and why he took his own life.
But in a note
found at the scene,
Kurt mentions, and I quote,
"his burning nauseous
stomach".
And this is a reference to
the chronic stomach pain
that was so debilitating that
he said it blighted his life.
So could this be the reason
he attempted suicide in Rome
and finally took his life
a month later?
'Kurt's parents' marriage
started to collapse
when Kurt was seven.
By the time he was nine,
and they divorced,
their break-up was having
a devastating effect on him.'
(IAN) When his parents split,
he started to change.
'Cause for any kid,
it's not easy.
And that's sort of when the
stomach pain first surfaced.
He had stomach problems
from an early age.
And it wasn't diagnosed.
If you look at any of the
seminal moments in his life,
that stomach pain was there.
It may very well have been
that part of his condition
was psychosomatic.
We know that being in
emotional turmoil
makes physical pain
feel worse.
So it wouldn't be
shocking to assume
that his mental state did
affect his physical state.
(IAN) It haunted him,
because he couldn't function
properly in everyday life.
He really felt that...
..unless he got rid of
the stomach pain,
basically, life was over.
I can see from Kurt's records
that he was treated
for his stomach condition.
And he also had three
endoscopic procedures
to try to determine precisely
the cause of his pain.
An endoscopy is where
a small camera is inserted
through the mouth and then
moved down the throat
into the esophagus, stomach
and upper gastro-intestinal
tract.
The camera relays the images
back to the screen,
where the doctor
can see inside the body
in great detail.
'But despite having three
endoscopic examinations,
the doctors could find
no explanation
for Kurt's chronic
stomach pain,
leading him to speculate
on its causes.'
(KURT) Every time
I've had an endoscope,
they find a red irritation
in my stomach.
But it's just um...
It's psychosomatic.
It's all
from anger and screaming.
I mean, my mom had it when
she was in her early 20s
for a few years and it just
eventually went away.
She was in the hospital
all the time because of it.
Stomach pain obviously
ran in the Cobain family.
But in Kurt's case, it's
because of his scoliosis.
This condition can pinch
abdominal nerves,
causing severe stomach pain.
In 1993,
when it was discovered
that this was the reason
for his abdominal pain,
a simple prescription
appears to have
brought the condition
under control.
So I don't believe this is
responsible for his death.
Kurt was a frequent
heroin user
and claimed that he took it
to treat his abdominal pain.
So I want to investigate
what role this drug played
in his death.
(VO) Dogs have evolved,
but their nutritional needs
remain instinctual.
That's why there's
Purina ONE True Instinct.
High protein for
strong muscles.
A different breed of
natural nutrition.
Purina ONE True Instinct.
Also in Grain-Free
for dogs and cats.
So nice to meet you June, Jay,
Ji, Kay, Raj, and...Ray!
Good job, Brain!
Say hello to Neuriva, a new
brain supplement
with clinically proven
ingredients
that fuel five indicators of
brain performance.
Neuriva.
parodontax Complete Protection
If you see traces of blood
when you brush or floss,
which kind of toothpaste
do you choose?
One for healthy gums?
Or one for strong teeth?
You don't have to choose.
Complete Protection
from parodontax
has 8 designed benefits
for healthy gums
and strong teeth.
Take control
and leave bleeding gums behind
with Complete Protection
from parodontax.
♪
Give Extra, get extra
with new Extra Refreshers gum.
♪
When you get right down to it...
Freedom is the ability to go
where you wanna go...
♪
and do what you wanna do.
So... what do you wanna do?
The 2019 Jeep Compass.
Hurry in to the 4th of July
Sales Event and get $500
additional bonus cash
on select models.
Visit Jeep.com
Are you a sunrise
cycle snacker?
An afternoon
multitasker snacker?
Or a midnight movie
attacker watcher snacker?
What ever type of
snacker you are.
Sargento Balanced Breaks
are a perfectly balanced
snack anytime of day.
Made with natural cheese and
other delicious ingredients.
So even if you're
a tarmac snacker.
A balanced six pack snacker.
A backpack packer snacker.
Or a lumberjack on horseback
in a cul de sac snacker.
Sargento Balanced Breaks
are the snack for you.
Sargento.
We're real cheese people.
'Expert coroner and forensic
pathologist Dr. Michael
Hunter
is examining all the
available medical evidence
about the death of the
musical icon and prince
of grunge, Kurt Cobain.
He was found dead
in his Seattle mansion,
with a gunshot wound
to his head.
For over 20 years,
controversy
has surrounded his death,
with many refusing
to believe it was suicide.
Now Dr. Hunter plans to
finally get to the bottom
of what really killed
Kurt Cobain.'
When Kurt returned from Rome,
his heroin use increased.
He was using about $400 worth
of heroin every day.
And that's $700
in today's prices.
This is an enormous amount
of heroin to take on
a daily basis.
And those who were close
to him realized
that if they didn't
do something,
Kurt was gonna die.
'Seattle, Washington.
Ten days before
Kurt Cobain's death.
Kurt walks
into his living room
having just injected heroin
and gets a surprise.'
- You need to change.
- Change?
An intervention was organized
by his entertainment attorney
Rosemary Carroll and her
husband Danny Goldberg.
Several of his closest
people were there,
including his best friends.
(MAN) We all care about you,
dude.
They thought Kurt
was in a dark zone.
They thought he was doing
too much heroin.
'But the intervention
backfires,
with Kurt accusing his
friends of being hypocrites,
for also using drugs
while telling him
to stop taking them.'
No, we take drugs,
we play guitar...
We're not talking about a
bit of party coke but about
life and death.
Talking about our baby, yes.
Tell me I'm wrong.
It's pretty hard for
somebody to tell a drug user
that they shouldn't
be using it.
That's where they find
their peace.
I'm sure he did not want
to stop using
and that's one of the reasons
he got angry about it.
You know,
"Don't tell me what to do!"
This isn't funny anymore.
'By now, Kurt's excessive
drug-taking has not only
alienated all of his friends
but his marriage to Courtney
is also on the rocks.'
Hypocrites, hypocrites,
hypocrites!
Every single one of you,
dammit!
I believe Kurt's adverse
reaction to the intervention
is because he didn't see
himself as a drug addict.
He claims he was using
heroin not for enjoyment
but for medicinal reasons.
I've had this stomach
condition for years.
There were times,
especially during touring
and while off a tour,
where I just felt
like a drug addict
because I was starving
and I went to all these
different doctors
and they couldn't find out
what was wrong with me.
I tried everything.
Nothing worked.
And I just decided that
if I'm gonna feel like
a junkie every morning,
vomiting every day,
then I may as well, you know,
take a substance
that kills that pain.
(CHRISTOPHER) Kurt initially
got into heroin
because it seemed to him
to be a painkiller.
His whole teenage years,
he was looking for various
pills and prescriptions
to help get over his bad
back, his bad stomach.
I think the idea of taking
a drug to escape pain
is something that
one hears very often.
And while that is,
I guess, understandable
in the short term,
it doesn't negate the fact
that it's still a choice.
The excuse of, "I had no
choice because I was in pain"
is one that again you hear -
a lot of that excusing.
Kurt's explanation that he
used heroin for pain relief
may be true.
But the damage that
that drug caused
far outweighed
any conceived benefit.
But I've found something
else in Kurt's background
that might also explain
his reliance on chemical
stimulants.
'In 1974, aged seven,
Kurt's manic behavior
worried his parents
to such an extent that
he is taken to the doctor's,
where he's diagnosed with
attention deficit
hyperactivity disorder -
or ADHD -
and prescribed
the drug Ritalin.'
Here you had
an artistic kid,
who's a little bit different
to begin with, and wants to
rather draw than do his math
and that sort of thing.
He may be acting out a bit
because of his home life,
so they did put him
on Ritalin.
Ritalin is the common name
for the drug Methylphenidate
and it's classified by
the Drug Enforcement
Administration
as a Schedule II drug,
in the same classification
as, say, cocaine,
morphine and amphetamines.
Ritalin works
by increasing the activity
of the chemicals
dopamine and/or adrenaline
in areas of the brain
that play a part
in controlling attention
and behavior.
(CHRISTOPHER) He was first
prescribed Ritalin
and you can see that
that might have started
a life-time habit
of relying on various drugs
to balance his mood out.
Along with the Ritalin
there came sleeping pills
because he couldn't sometimes
go to bed at night -
even as a youngster.
So already you can begin
to see where there's
a certain amount
of chemical assistance
going on, just to get him
through the day.
'After his parents' divorce,
Kurt stayed with
each of them,
but following
continual arguments,
both asked him to leave.
At 15 years old,
Kurt Cobain was homeless
and his ADHD
was going untreated.
Over the next four years,
Kurt had ten different homes.
He would stay at friends'
houses and sleep in hallways,
abandoned properties
or under a bridge.
As Kurt increasingly
dropped out of society,
he had run-ins with the law
and was arrested
for vandalism.
For a decade,
his ADHD went untreated
and his addiction to heroin
reached dangerous levels.'
There is no evidence to
suggest that Ritalin itself
leads to addiction.
But children with ADHD
are two to three times
more likely
to have substance abuse
issues later in life.
But after a life-time
of relying on drugs
to treat pain
and to alter his moods,
Kurt finally agrees to seek
treatment for his addiction
to heroin.
'Four days before
Kurt Cobain's death.
Kurt has been at the Exodus
Recovery Center for 24 hours.
But despite his promise to
seek help for his addiction,
he decides he doesn't want to
continue with the treatment.'
The problem with
the Exodus Center
is it has no
physical constraint
to keep the person there if
he doesn't want to be there.
Kurt climbed over a wall
because he missed
his daughter,
several of his close friends.
He felt it was the time
to restart life.
'But Kurt's cousin Beverly
thinks he fled rehab
for very different reasons.'
There was a chance that he
could have been really helped
in that facility,
but he apparently did not
want to stop using heroin.
It may very well have been
that the prospect
of coming off heroin
was scary for Kurt.
This was one of his
coping mechanisms.
This was one of the tools
that helped get him
through the day.
In his mind,
this was one of the tools
that kept the pain away,
that helped the creativity,
that kept him stable
in some ways.
So, one of
the biggest barriers
to him actually seeking
the help that he did
may have been this fear
of what it was like
to live without the heroin.
I can see from the report
that drug paraphernalia
was found at the scene
of Kurt's death.
He also had
a blood morphine level
of 1.52 milligrams
per liter -
and that is
a tremendous amount.
So the question I have is:
what happened to Kurt from
the time that he left rehab
and when he died
four days later?
'The Peninsula Hotel,
Beverly Hills.
Two days before
Kurt Cobain's death.'
(Indistinct chatter)
'Private Detective Tom Grant
and his assistant
are summoned by
Kurt's wife Courtney.
She tells him
Kurt has fled rehab
and bought a shotgun -
and could be suicidal.'
Tom Grant was briefed
to check around
for Kurt's whereabouts.
He was meant to go to
the house in Seattle
and find Kurt.
Six days after Kurt
went missing,
private investigator
Tom Grant searches
his Seattle mansion...
but doesn't find him.'
Kurt?
'Seven days after Kurt's
disappearance from rehab.
An electrician is
installing security lights
on the building
above Kurt's garage.'
The private eye and the
others, the Seattle police,
had not thought to check
that particular building,
but Gary Smith,
the electrician,
went up there
and he saw Kurt's body
lying on the floor.
'The electrician
calls the police.
At 9am, paramedic John Fisk
arrives at the property.
When we arrived at the scene,
we did not know
whose house it was.
We were directed by
the police officer
up around the garage.
I was probably the first one
to arrive at the door.
We could see a body
laying inside
with a gun evident
in his lap.
I don't believe we could tell
whether it had just happened,
if he could still be alive.
But I told the police officer
we needed to get in there
right away,
indicating to him that
I hoped he would perform
some forcible entry.
He felt that they needed
to wait for a supervisor.
We felt we didn't have
the time.
As we entered the room
and approached the body,
it was evident
that he was dead
and there was nothing
we could do for him.
It would appear that he had
been sitting on the floor
with his legs out,
a shotgun between his legs,
and activated the trigger,
perhaps with his thumb
or something.
The wound was in his mouth.
The exit wound to the back,
left side of his head.
His face wasn't badly
distorted or misshapen,
like we often see
with a gunshot wound
to the head.
We are working on a
presumptive identification,
but until we confirm
and notify the family,
we will not release the name.
(BEV) The phone rang and it
was a newspaper reporter
and he told me that
somebody had killed themself
in Kurt's garage.
And um...
And I said,
"Well, it can't be Kurt
because he's in treatment."
And he said, "No, no, he
left there a few days ago."
I sort of put
two and two together
and I went on my knees
and um...sobbed.
(REPORTER) Kurt Cobain's
body was found inside
a garage apartment
adjacent to his Seattle home,
dead of an apparently
self-inflicted shotgun wound.
(JAMES) It came on the radio
and I was really depressed.
It immediately makes you
remember that person
that tugged my arm
at the show
and said,
"Hey, how you doing?"
Just this cute, little guy,
you know.
Plus, I was really enjoying
his music
and imagining how far
he could take it.
A postmortem confirmed
that Kurt Cobain died from
a single shot to the head
by a 20-gauge
Remington shotgun
that he'd purchased only
eight days before he died.
'Kurt's body was found to
the left of the greenhouse,
on its back, with a shotgun
laying on his chest.
The barrel had been placed
in his mouth
and the trigger pulled,
discharging hundreds
of small lead shot
through the roof of his mouth
and into his brain.
The damage was catastrophic.'
A single shot fired
in Kurt Cobain's mouth
would have killed him
instantly.
And given the fact that
there is a suicide note,
this appears to be
an open and shut case.
'But, since the death,
many have refused to accept
it was a suicide
and believe
Kurt was murdered.
They claim to have
irrefutable evidence
that this is the case.
So could Kurt Cobain
have really been murdered?
And, if so, by whom?'
♪
Protect your pet
with the #1 name
in flea and tick protection.
FRONTLINE Plus.
Trusted by vets
for nearly 20 years.
If your dishwasher doesn't get
dishes completely dry...
try Finish Jet-Dry's NEW
stronger formula.
It dries 100% better than
detergent alone - even plastics.
Get dishes drier than you ever
thought possible.
Try Finish Jet-Dry.
I can't tell you who I am
or what I witnessed,
but I can tell you Liberty
Mutual customized my
car insurance so I only
pay for what I need.
Oh no, no, no, no,
no, no, no...
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
How did we test our
Dixie Ultra plates?
With two pounds of steak.
In each hand.
Dixie Ultra.
Stress tested so you can
stress less at dinner.
♪
Oh, Pete!?!
C'mon man.
What? We said pantyhose right?
Here, eat this...
Creamy SNICKERS®.
You could use
a little smoothness.
Pete? Pete Zagorin?
Get smooth with the fresh-ground
nut butters
in new Creamy SNICKERS®.
This, is why we no longer have
to worry
about flushing too much toilet
paper.
Rid-X contains billions of
enzymes
proven to break down even paper
to keep your whole septic system
healthy.
Rid-X, the number 1 septic
brand.
Also from Rid-X, try NEW RV Odor
control.
What makes DiGiorno Crispy Pan
Pizza different than delivery?
♪ PAN PAN PAN PAAAAN
You bake it fresh
in its own pan!
Giving our DiGiorno pizza
a crispy, caramelized crust.
♪ PAAAAN
It's not Delivery,
It's DiGiorno.
I've been saying,
“I'm fine.”
But, really I'm struggling to
keep up this brave face...
to hide my symptoms
of depression.
I'm taking my antidepressant
like we discussed.
But, I'm still feeling
depressed.
Is it just me?
It's not just you.
2 out of 3 people
on antidepressants
may still experience symptoms.
When added to an
antidepressant,...
REXULTI has been proven to help
reduce symptoms of depression.
So I can stay on my current
antidepressant...
and help build on the
progress I've made.
REXULTI is not for everyone.
Call your doctor about unusual
changes in behavior,
worsening depression,
or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants can increase
these in those 24 and younger.
Elderly dementia patients
taking REXULTI
have an increased risk
of death or stroke.
Call your doctor if you
have high fever,
stiff muscles, and confusion
to address a possible
life-threatening condition...
or if you have uncontrollable
muscle movements,
as these may be permanent.
REXULTI has been shown
to increase blood sugar
in some people.
Other risks are increased
cholesterol; weight gain;
unusual urges or
compulsive behaviors; ...
decreased white blood cells,
which can be serious; ...
dizziness on standing; seizures;
trouble swallowing;
and impaired judgment
or motor skills.
Now, I'm glad I talked with my
doctor about adding REXULTI.
Feel better about
facing the world.
Pay $0 for your first
REXULTI prescription.
Details at REXULTI.com.
'Kurt Cobain's sudden death
at the age of 27
sent shockwaves
around the world.
The official verdict
was that he died
as a result of suicide
from a gunshot wound
to the head.
But this verdict
has been challenged
by those who don't believe
Kurt Cobain's death
was a suicide.
Now Dr. Michael Hunter
plans to uncover
what really happened
in Kurt Cobain's final hours,
to reveal the true cause
of his death.'
Kurt Cobain's body
lay undiscovered
for three days
following his death
and the autopsy revealed
the presence of
1.52 milligrams per liter
of morphine in the blood.
In the body, heroin
breaks down into morphine
and this is
an incredibly high level.
So, some have argued
that it is so high,
it would have been
impossible for Kurt
to have the time
to shoot himself
before passing out.
Therefore, foul play
must have been involved.
'One person who believed
that Kurt was murdered
was the family member
he was closest to -
his grandfather, Leland.'
He had so much dope in him
that he couldn't have
possibly
brought that shotgun up.
And that's why I think
he was murdered.
'Courtney Love's
estranged father
also believes
Kurt was killed.'
I knew from the beginning,
maybe six months into it,
that Kurt had been murdered.
The little box that he had
had Mexican tar heroin in it.
You can't shoot up
enough Mexican tar heroin
to get that much heroin
in your bloodstream.
All the junkies I've talked
to said, "Oh, no.
That's absolutely
impossible."
'More surprisingly,
Hank Harrison believes
his daughter could be
implicated in the murder.
He's had a tumultuous
relationship with Courtney
since his divorce
from her mother...
and believes she had
a motive to want Kurt dead.'
There was a prenup
and she was only gonna get
a small amount of money
and Kurt had already
asked for a divorce
and a change in the will.
'Investigative journalist
Ian Halperin
has been following the story
for more than 20 years.'
(IAN) If Kurt died,
she would inherit
the whole Cobain estate
to the tune of $100 million.
And if they would've
divorced,
she would've walked away
with nothing
because of the prenup.
'He also believes
that it would be impossible
for Kurt to shoot himself
with such a high level
of heroin in his system,
and argues that there are
other highly-suspicious
inconsistencies
surrounding
Kurt Cobain's death.'
Kurt's body was found
lying with a shotgun.
Whomever killed him
had gloves on.
There were no
latent fingerprints
found on the gun.
Dead men don't wipe
their own prints.
'It's also argued
there are inconsistencies
in the handwriting
on the suicide note.'
I hired the two top
handwriting experts
in the world
to study the suicide note
and to dissect it.
They said it was written in
two different handwritings.
The top of the note
was written in Kurt's
handwriting.
And the bottom of the note -
the last five lines -
which dealt with the suicide,
was written in the
handwriting of somebody else.
'And those that believe
Kurt was killed...
think this is how
it happened.'
Kurt was assassinated, but
he didn't die all at once.
Whoever killed him
did it in stages.
First thing you do is
incapacitate the person.
After he was knocked out
with Rohypnol...
..he got shot up with
what we think to be
a massive dose of fentanyl.
He died.
They had to give him
a shotgun
and shoot him to make it
look like it was an absolute
prima facie case of suicide.
(Gunshot)
Fentanyl is a powerful
synthetic painkiller,
similar to morphine,
but a hundred times
more potent.
And the autopsy also revealed
the presence of a
diazepam-like substance.
And this could
possibly be Rohypnol.
(IAN) The smoking gun
is the heroin level.
70 times the lethal dose
for the average person.
Three times
for the most severe junkie.
Forensic pathological
experts say
there's never been
one case documented
in the history of humankind
with so much heroin
in somebody's system.
Kurt did have an
exceptionally high level
of heroin in his system
when he died.
But, I believe there's
an explanation for this
and the other factors
people point to
as proof of foul play.
After shotgun deaths
there is a lot of blood loss.
And the medical examiner
may only be able to get blood
from the heart sample.
As Kurt shot himself soon
after injecting the heroin,
it hadn't had a chance
to distribute
throughout his body.
The veins drained directly
into the heart,
so the drug
is concentrated there.
Giving a much higher reading
than normal.
The lack of fingerprints
can also be explained.
The police report says that
they took four latent prints
but they were of poor quality
and couldn't be identified.
Now keep in mind, the gun
had lain for three days
in a damp environment.
And this is not good
for fingerprints.
And I believe
this explains why the police
were unable to find usable
prints on that weapon.
Finally, the differences
in the handwriting
on the suicide note
are notable.
But I think
you can look at this
and see that in the latter
part of the note
Kurt wrote this while
under the influence of drugs.
And a police expert
looked at this
and confirmed
that this indeed
was the handwriting
of Kurt Cobain.
For these reasons
I believe that Kurt Cobain
did indeed kill himself.
And I think I've discovered
the reason why.
♪  ♪
Discover new
San Pellegrino Essenza.
A twist of
Mediterranean flavors,
with the gentle bubbles
of San Pellegrino.
Add a twist of flavor.
San Pellegrino Essenza.
Tastefully Italian.
When you start with a better
hot dog from Oscar Mayer...
That's no way to treat a dog...
...you can do no wrong.
Where did you learn that?
The internet...
Yeah?
MMM!
With no artificial preservatives
or added nitrates or nitrites,
it's all for the love
of hot dogs.
Ok. It was an accident.
He was tickling me and...
[laughing] Stop it!
Yeah.
Whoops!
But Julie has Resolve Pet
Expert.
Its latest formula attacks
odors at the source.
No odor. No stain. No nothin'.
Whatever happens, no
big deal. Resolve.
It's about time they gave
Left and Right TWIX®
their own packs.
They got about
as much in common
as you, a mortician,
and me, an undertaker.
(Chuckling)
Or you, a janitor,
and me, a custodian.
(Laughing)
Or you, a ghost,
and me, a spirit.
(Laughing)
Left and Right TWIX® packs.
It's time to deSide.
♪
Protect your pet
with the #1 name
in flea and tick protection.
FRONTLINE Plus.
Trusted by vets
for nearly 20 years.
'Kurt Cobain died
from a single shotgun
wound to the head,
in what police said
was a suicide.
Many people have disputed
this conclusion,
using the level of morphine
found in Kurt's body
to argue it would
have been impossible
for him to have time to load
a gun and shoot himself.'
(Gunshot)
I have shown how
the length of time
that Kurt Cobain
went undiscovered,
and the location where
the blood sample was taken,
could have had an effect
on the toxicology analysis.
So I am ruling out foul play
as being involved
in some way with his death.
I believe that Kurt Cobain
did indeed kill himself.
And the evidence for this
rests in his family history.
We know that Kurt
was diagnosed at age nine
with ADHD - attention deficit
hyperactivity disorder.
What wasn't known is that
he was also likely suffering
from bipolar disorder.
And that used to be known
as manic depression.
Kurt's mother told me
he suffered from
bipolar disorder
and it made sense
when you saw
how he was doing kind of
wild, crazy things.
Because that
typifies bipolar disorder.
It's a mood disorder that's
punctuated by this very
polarized way of behaving.
This kind of addicted
workaholic that, you know,
wouldn't stop, wanted
to get things to perfection.
Wanted to find
the best drummers,
wanted to find the
best riffs, wanted to make
the most amazing music.
And then this other side,
which was a depressive,
that just felt
never quite good enough.
It's a very difficult
condition to live with.
And one that needs both
proper medication
and proper
psychological support.
I've not been able to find
any evidence that Kurt Cobain
was ever treated
for bipolar disorder.
But...I have discovered
that depression and suicide
ran in the Cobain family.
I have lost two uncles
and then Kurt.
They were the same age
when they killed themselves,
because I remember
Uncle Leland saying,
"Oh, my gosh, in a few years
I'll be that age."
And he was worried that
he would kill himself then.
I've also discovered that
the chronic stomach pain
that Kurt thought
he had been cured of
had returned in the weeks
prior to his death.
I think the reason
that Kurt killed himself
can be
summed up in one word: pain.
He was in such pain -
both emotional,
psychological, and physical -
that he just could not
stand it any more.
He'd rather be dead
than alive.
It's one of those terrible
ironies of his life.
That he worked so hard
to become something.
And then once he did
he didn't like it very much.
I sincerely believe
that Kurt committed suicide.
He clearly was not happy,
running away, hiding.
Upping his usage,
not trusting anyone.
Kurt did appear happy
in the months before he died.
'Ever since I've been married
and I've had a child,
I've never been
more optimistic.'
But I think
this was a facade.
When you see that kind
of happiness in somebody
that you know has
been suicidal - watch out!
Because that usually means
they have made the decision
to kill themselves, and now
they're feeling relief.
Having considered all of
the medical evidence,
I believe suicide
is the best explanation
for Kurt Cobain's death.
And this, I think,
is how it happened.
'The day
of Kurt Cobain's death.
Kurt removes
the 20-gauge shotgun
from its hiding place
in his closet
and heads to the room
above his garage.
Once there he finishes
his suicide note.
Which he leaves
in a planting tray
and spears with
the red ballpoint pen
it's written in.
He unzips the bag
holding his shotgun.
He takes three cartridges out
of a box and loads the gun.
He smokes five cigarettes
as he sits on the floor
before preparing
his final hit of heroin.
It contains
so much of the drug
that, once injected, it would
kill him within a minute.
After injecting the heroin,
Kurt places the gun barrel
in his mouth
- and pulls the trigger.
- (Gunshot)
He dies instantly.'
I believe that
Kurt Cobain killed himself
while suffering from
the untreated effects
of his mental illness -
bipolar disorder.
His depressed mental state
was further exacerbated
by the physical pain
of his stomach condition
and the decline in his mental
and physical state
from his excessive use
of heroin.
'Kurt's death left a
generation in mourning.
But his image...
untarnished by age and time.'
He'd be turning 50
and you can speculate
on what it was
he'd be doing
had he lived...
But doing the nostalgia tour
with Nirvana,
slightly fatter and balder,
playing all their old hits,
I don't think he would have
gone for that.