>> THIS IS "BBC WORLD NEWS
AMERICA."
FUNDING OF THIS PRESENTATION IS
MADE POSSIBLE BY
THE FREEMAN FOUNDATION,
AND KOVLER FOUNDATION, PURSUING
SOLUTIONS FOR AMERICA'S
NEGLECTED NEEDS.
>> WOW, THAT IS UNBELIEVABLE.
♪
>> I'M FLYING!
>> STAY CURIOUS.
♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> AND NOW, "BBC WORLD NEWS."
LS
AMERICA."
REPORTING FROM WASHINGTON, I AM
LAURA TREVELYAN.
COUNTDOWN TO THE STATE OF THE
UNION ADDRESS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WILL CALL FOR
UNITY IN FRONT OF A DEEPLY
DIVIDED CONGRESS.
>> MR. NEESON, ARE YOU SORRY FOR
WHAT YOU SAID?
LAURA: ACTOR LIAM NEESON SAYS HE
IS NO RACIST AFTER HIS DESIRE
FOR REVENGE CAUSES AN UPROAR.
>> VERY FIRST PICTURE I TOOK.
LAURA: PLUS, DON MCCULLIN'S
CAMERA CAPTURED THE HUMAN COST
OF BATTLE.
WE HEAR HOW HE TURNED HIS LENS
ON THE HOME FRONT, TOO.
LAURA: WELCOME TO OUR VIEWERS ON
PUBLIC TELEVISION IN THE U.S.
AND AROUND THE GLOBE.
WASHINGTON IS POISED FOR
TONIGHT'S STATE OF THE UNION
ADDRESS BY PRESIDENT TRUMP.
AIDES SAY HE WILL CALL FOR
BIPARTISAN COOPERATION AND
UNITY.
BUT MR. TRUMP WILL DELIVER HIS
PRIMETIME ADDRESS TO A DIVIDED
CONGRESS WHILE STILL SMARTING
AFTER THE GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN
OVER THE PRESIDENTS CALL FOR A
BORDER WALL WITH MEXICO.
KATTY KAY JOINED ME EARLIER.
WHITE HOUSE AIDES HAVE SAID THIS
IS GOING TO BE ABOUT COMITY, BUT
GIVEN HOW DIVIDED THE TWO SIDES
ARE, CAN ANYTHING BE ACHIEVED?
KATTY: LOOK, I THINK WHAT THE
PRESIDENT WANTS TO DO TONIGHT IS
REACH OUT TO VOTERS IN THE
MIDDLE WITH SOME SORT OF UNITY
AND BIPARTISANSHIP.
WE WILL HEAR THAT TOWNE --
TONE.
IT IS BEING WRITTEN INTO HIS
SPEECH AT THE MOMENT.
AND ALSO APPEAL TO HIS BASE WITH
A TOUGHER LINE ON IMMIGRATION
AND THE BORDER WALL.
PRESIDENT TRUMP KNOWS HE WILL
NOT GET A TELEVISION AUDIENCE
THIS BIG AGAIN UNTIL THE 2020
REELECTION CAMPAIGN IS WELL
UNDERWAY.
AND SO HE  HAS GOT THAT
POLITICAL TIMETABLE IN MIND.
JUGGLING THOSE TWO THINGS IS
GOING TO BE TRICKY IN TERMS OF
TONE, AND WE KNOW WHAT IS SAID
IN A SPEECH TONIGHT ON CAPITOL
HILL COULD VERY QUICKLY BE
OVERTURNED WITH ONE TWEET
TOMORROW MORNING.
LAURA: IT CAN INDEED.
IS THIS LAYING OUT THE BATTLE
LINES FOR THE 2020 ELECTION?
KATTY: I THINK IT IS.
THERE ARE AREAS WHERE THE
PRESIDENT AND THE REPUBLICANS
AND THE DEMOCRATS DO AGREE.
THEY COULD DO A BIG DEAL ON
INFRASTRUCTURE.
I SUSPECT WE WILL HEAR THE
PRESIDENT REACH OUT TO DEMOCRATS
ON AN ISSUE LIKE THAT.
THE TROUBLE IS THERE IS SO
LITTLE TRUST ON THE DEMOCRATIC
SIDE OF THIS PRESIDENT THAT ARE
THEY WILLING TO GIVE HIM SOME
KIND OF DEAL THAT HE CAN TAKE
HOME AND SAY, LOOK, I'VE MANAGED
TO ACHIEVE SOMETHING?
THE 2020 REELECTION CAMPAIGN IN
A SENSE IS STARTING RIGHT NOW.
WE HAVE ALREADY HAD THOSE
DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES WHO HAVE
LAUNCHED THEIR BIDS.
THEY WILL BE SITTING RIGHT IN
FRONT OF THE PRESIDENT.
TONIGHT IS HIS BIG AUDIENCE TO
TALK ABOUT WHAT HE HAS ACHIEVED
AND WHAT HE CAN STILL ACHIEVE,
AND THE SPECTACLE OF THIS CROWD
-- CROWNED BY NANCY PELOSI
SITTING RIGHT BEHIND HIM, THE
DEMOCRAT WHO HAS JUST GIVEN HIM
A TOUGH TIME, TOUGH RUN FOR HIS
MONEY OVER THE GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN.
YOU ARE RIGHT, THE 2020
REELECTION CAMPAIGN IS ALL OVER
THIS STATE OF THE NOON ADDRESS.
LAURA: WHAT WILL YOU BE WATCHING
FOR WHEN YOU SEE NANCY PELOSI
THERE, THE SYMBOL OF DIVIDED
GOVERNMENT WATCHING OVER THE
PRESIDENT?
KATTY: IT IS ALMOST A VISUAL
REMINDER IN EVERY SHOT, BECAUSE
IN THESE STATES OF THE UNIONS,
YOU HAVE THE PRESIDENT AND THEN
THE TWO PEOPLE, MIKE PENCE AND
NANCY PELOSI BEHIND HIM.
THEY ARE IN ALMOST EVERY SHOT.
IT IS ALMOST A VISUAL REMINDER
OF THIS NEW, TOUGHER POLITICAL
LANDSCAPE THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
FACES.
I WOULD BE SURPRISED IF SHE
GIVES HIM A MUCH MORE THAN A
CURSORY ROUND OF APPLAUSE IN THE
BEGINNING.
THE REST OF THE TIME I EXPECT
HER TO SIT STONEFACED WHILE
VICE PRESIDENT MIKE PENCE IT'S
THEIR CHEERING.
THAT IS THE KIND OF PROSPECT
THAT ALWAYS COMES UP IN STATES
OF THE UNION.
REMEMBER, IT IS NOT JUST NANCY
PELOSI SITTING BEHIND HIM.
IT IS ALL THOSE NEWLY ELECTED
MEMBERS OF THE DEMOCRATIC HOUSE
OF REPRESENTATIVES SITTING IN
FRONT OF HIM.
THIS IS A VERY DIFFERENT STATE
OF THE UNION AUDIENCE IN THAT
CHAMBER THAN IT WAS FOR HIM A
YEAR AGO.
LAURA: KATTY KAY, THANK YOU.
THE STATE OF THE UNION ADDRESS
IS A MARQUEE EVENT, A SPEECH
WHICH IS REWRITTEN MULTIPLE
TIMES.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS THE
PRESIDENT HAS BEEN GOING THROUGH
TONIGHT'S PAGES WITH HIS SHARPIE
REWORKING THE MATERIAL.
IT IS ALL ABOUT STRIKING THE
RIGHT TONE WHILE LEAVING AN
IMPRESSION FOR THE AGES.
HERE ARE EXAMPLES FROM THE PAST.
PRES. REAGAN: DON'T LET ANYONE
TELL YOU THAT AMERICA'S BEST
DAYS ARE BEHIND HER.
THAT THE AMERICAN SPIRIT HAS
BEEN VANQUISHED.
PRES. CLINTON: THE ERA OF BIG
GOVERNMENT IS OVER.
PRES. BUSH: THEIR TERRORIST
ALLIES CONSTITUTE AN AXIS OF
EVIL, ARMING TO THREATEN THE
PEACE OF THE WORLD.
LAURA: FOR MORE ON THE
SIGNIFICANCE OF THESE MAJOR
ADDRESSES AND THE WORK THAT GOES
INTO THEM, I SPOKE EARLIER WITH
STEPHEN KRUPIN, A FORMER
SPEECHWRITER FOR PRESIDENT
OBAMA.
THE STATE OF THE UNION ADDRESS
IS A HIGHLY CHOREOGRAPHED ONE.
JUST HOW HIGH ARE THE
EXPECTATIONS OF THIS SPEECH
TONIGHT?
STEPHEN: THE WHITE HOUSE WOULD
LIKE TO SET OUT AN EXPECTATION
THAT THIS IS GOING TO BE AS YOU
AND KATTY MENTIONED, A SPEECH OF
UNITY, WHICH IS AS CREDIBLE AS
MUCH ELSE FROM THE TRUMP WHITE
HOUSE.
THE STATE OF THE UNION ADDRESS
HAPPENS IN THE HOUSE CHAMBER.
IT DOESN'T HAPPEN IN A VACUUM.
WE CANNOT LISTEN TO WHAT HE SAYS
TONIGHT WITHOUT REGARD TO WHAT
HE SAID YESTERDAY AND WHAT HE
WILL SAY TOMORROW.
IF THE PRESIDENT CONTINUES TO
STIGMATIZE IMMIGRANTS AND SPURN
ALLIES, HOW IS THAT UNITY?
IF THE WHITE HOUSE GOES TO SUCH
EXTREMES TO MAKE THAT CASE THAT
THIS IS A CASE ABOUT UNITY, IF
HE DOES THAT ONE DAY A YEAR
USING SENTENCES THAT WE KNOW
DON'T SOUND THE WAY PRESIDENT
TRUMP AS WE ALL KNOW SOUNDS, IT
GIVES LIE TO THE WHOLE CHARADE.
LAURA: BUT AS A FORMER
SPEECHWRITER, HOW MUCH WORK
WOULD GO INTO A SPEECH LIKE
THIS?
STEPHEN: AN ENORMOUS AMOUNT OF
WORK.
IT STARTS MONTHS BEFORE THE
SPEECH ITSELF.
IT IS A SPEECH WHERE NOT ONLY
THE WHITE HOUSE IS FOCUSED ON
IT, THE COMMUNICATIONS, POLICY,
THE RESEARCH PARTS OF THE WHITE
HOUSE, BUT ALSO ALL THE CABINET
AGENCIES.
EVERYONE WANTS THEIR LINE IN
THAT PRECIOUS REAL ESTATE,
BECAUSE WHEN THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES SAYS IT TO THE
COUNTRY AND THE WORLD, IT
ELEVATES THEIR ISSUE.
LAURA: TYPICALLY THESE SPEECHES
HAS A BIG HISTORICAL SWEEP.
THE TRADITION BEGAN WITH GEORGE
WASHINGTON HIMSELF.
STEPHEN: IT IS.
IT IS HISTORICAL AND THE HISTORY
IS ALL ABOUT ACCOUNTABILITY.
IT IS NOT THE PRESIDENT SPEAKING
TO THE COUNTRY AND THE WORLD
FROM THE OVAL OFFICE.
IT IS THE PRESIDENT COMING TO
THE PEOPLE'S HOUSE AT THE
INVITATION OF THE PEOPLE'S
HOUSE, WHICH UNDERSCORES THAT
OUR DEMOCRACY IS ABOUT CHECKS
AND BALANCES, AND THE PRESIDENT
WHETHER HE LIKES IT OR NOT NEEDS
CONGRESS TO PASS HIS AGENDA.
LAURA: ALTHOUGH WE HEAR FROM THE
PRESIDENT, ESPECIALLY THIS ONE,
IN A VARIETY OF WAYS ON TWITTER
AND IMPROMPTU PRESS CONFERENCES,
AS AN OCCASION DO YOU THINK THE
STATE OF THE UNION RETAINS ITS
POWER?
STEPHEN: I THINK IT RETAINS ITS
POWER IN A GENERAL SENSE BECAUSE
OF THE PRESIDENT SPEAKING TO ALL
OF THE GOVERNMENT ASSEMBLED, AS
WELL AS THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
BEYOND AND AROUND THE WORLD.
IN THIS PARTICULAR CASE, I THINK
IT DOES HIM A DISSERVICE.
I THINK THE STATE OF THE UNION
IS HIS MOST UNNATURAL VENUE.
IT IS AT ITS BEST AN OPPORTUNITY
TO CALL FOR UNITY, WHICH
PRESIDENT TRUMP DOES NOT DO.
HE SPEAKS TO HIS BASE, HE IS
DIVISIVE.
IT IS AN OPPORTUNITY TO SPEAK
THE TRUTH, WHICH PRESIDENT TRUMP
DOESN'T DO.
IT IS AN OPPORTUNITY FOR CAREFUL
RHETORIC, AND PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
CARELESS AT BEST WITH HIS
RHETORIC.
LAURA: WE WILL SEE HOW HE DOES
TONIGHT.
PRESIDENT RONALD REAGAN STARTED
THIS TRADITION OF MENTIONING IN
HIS SPEECH PEOPLE HE BROUGHT AS
GUESTS, AND IT HAS BECOME
QUITE A BIT OF STAGECRAFT.
STEPHEN: IT IS ABSOLUTELY
STAGECRAFT.
IT IS AN IMPORTANT WAY TO SHOW
THAT THE POLICY SPOKEN ABOUT IN
THE ADDRESS ACTUALLY AFFECTS
REAL PEOPLE, REAL AMERICANS, NOT
JUST ABSTRACT POLITICAL THEORY
.
WHAT PRESIDENT OBAMA TRIED TO DO
WAS TALK ABOUT PEOPLE WHO
REPRESENTED THE STRUGGLES OR THE
CHALLENGES OR THE ASPIRATIONS
THAT THE AMERICAN PEOPLE WERE
GOING THROUGH.
IN 2015 THERE WAS A FAMILY FROM
MINNESOTA WHOSE STORY OF
PERSEVERANCE WAS A NICE METAPHOR
FOR THE WAY THE COUNTRY WAS
COMING OUT OF THE GREAT
RECESSION.
WHAT WAS DIFFERENT ABOUT THE WAY
PRESIDENT OBAMA USED THESE
GUESTS IS IT SPOKE TO THE
COUNTRY'S HOPES.
PRESIDENT TRUMP OFTEN USES THEM
EXPLOITATIVE WAY TO SPEAK OF
-- TO OUR FEARS.
LAURA: WE WILL SEE WHAT THE
SPEECH DOES TONIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
STEPHEN: GOOD TO BE HERE.
LAURA: THE ACTOR LIAM NEESON
SAYS HE IS NO RACIST AFTER
ADMITTING HE ONCE  WALKED
TO THE STREETS LOOKING FOR A
BLACK MAN TO KILL.
HE DESCRIBED A PRIMAL URGE FOR
REVENGE AFTER A FRIEND WAS
RAPED.
THE BBC'S NICK BRYANT HAS MORE
FROM NEW YORK.
NICK: AFTER HIS EXPLOSIVE
COMMENTS ABOUT RACE AND REVENGE,
--
MR. NEESON, ARE YOU SORRY FOR
WHAT YOU SAID?
MR. NEESON ARRIVED AT THIS NEW
YORK TELEVISION STUDIO NOT TO
MAKE AN APOLOGY BUT TO OFFER A
EXPLANATION.
HE ADMITTED TO SETTING OUT TO
KILL AN INNOCENT BLACK MAN
NEARLY 40 YEARS AGO AFTER
SOMEONE CLOSE TO HIM WAS
ALLEGEDLY RAPED BY A BLACK MAN.
>> WOULD YOU HAVE HAD THE SAME
REACTION IF IT WAS A WHITE MAN?
LIAM: IRISH OR SCOT OR
LITHUANIAN, I KNOW IT WOULD HAVE
HAD THE SAME EFFECT.
I WAS TRYING TO SHOW HONOR AND
STAND UP FOR MY DEAR FRIEND, IN
THIS TERRIBLE, MEDIEVAL FASHION.
I'M A FAIRLY INTELLIGENT GUY.
THAT IS WHY IT KIND OF SHOCKED
ME WHEN I CAME DOWN TO EARTH
AFTER HAVING THESE HORRIBLE
FEELINGS.
LUCKILY, NO VIOLENCE OCCURRED,
EVER.
THANKS BE TO GOD.
>> WHAT MAKES YOU THINK YOU CAN
KILL A MAN?
>> READ IT IN A CRIME NOVEL.
NICK: PROMOTING HIS NEW MOVIE,
THE THEME OF WHICH IS MURDEROUS
REVENGE, THE ACTOR HAD GIVEN AN
INTERVIEW TELLING HOW HE SOUGHT
RETRIBUTION AFTER HEARING ABOUT
THE RAPE.
LIAM: I ASKED, DID YOU KNOW WHO
HE WAS?
"NO."
COLOR?
SHE SAID IT WAS A BLACK PERSON.
I WENT UP AND DOWN AREAS WITH A
COSH HOPING I WOULD BE
APPROACHED BY SOME -- I'M
ASHAMED TO SAY THAT.
AND I DID IT FOR MAYBE A WEEK,
HOPING THAT SOME BLACK [BLEEP]
WOULD COME OUT OF A PUB, SO I
COULD KILL HIM.
NICK: THERE HAS BEEN OUTRAGE AT
THOSE REMARKS, BUT SOME HAVE
COMMENDED HIS HONESTY, AND
VIEWERS SAW HIS PERSONAL TORMENT
WRITTEN ACROSS HIS FACE.
>> I'M JUST SHOCKED.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE HE WOULD SAY
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I THOUGHT HE WAS A GOOD GUY.
>> IT MAKES YOU HAVE A LITTLE
BIT OF FEAR, BUT WE HAVE TO PUSH
THROUGH THAT AND FIND THE LOVE.
NICK: AT THIS BLACK THEATER
COMPANY IN LONDON, YOUNG ACTORS
GAVE US THEIR REACTION.
>> HIM USING THAT LANGUAGE IN
THE INTERVIEW IN LIGHT OF HIS
INFLUENCE IS NAÏVE.
>> I AGREE WITH YOU.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD VILIFY
HIM, BUT THE STATEMENT HE MADE
IS PROBLEMATIC.
NICK: FOR LIAM NEESON, TODAY WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE ABOUT PROMOTING
HIS NEW MOVIE, BUT INSTEAD HE IS
TRYING TO SALVAGE HIS
REPUTATION.
THE 66-YEAR-OLD HAS BEEN ONE OF
HOLLYWOOD'S MORE BANKABLE STARS.
WILL HE FACE A BACKLASH AT THE
BOX OFFICE?
NICK BRYANT, BBC NEWS, NEW YORK.
LAURA: IN OTHER NEWS, HIGH-LEVEL
TALKS BETWEEN AFGHAN OFFICIALS
AND THE TALIBAN ARE TAKING PLACE
IN RUSSIA, COMING OFF THE BACK
OF THE U.S. AND TALIBAN
ANNOUNCING THEY HAVE MADE
PROGRESS IN PEACE TALKS LAST
MONTH.
AFGHAN GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS, ONE
-- WHO ARE NOT TAKING PART IN
THE TALKS, CRITICIZED THE
MEETING AS COUNTERPRODUCTIVE.
A FORMER MANCHESTER UNITED
MANAGER HAS BEEN SENTENCED TO A
YEAR IN PRISON IN SPAIN FOR TAX
FRAUD, BUT WILL NOT SPEND ANY
TIME BEHIND BARS.
HE ACCEPTED THE SENTENCE AS PART
OF A DEAL WITH PROSECUTORS INTO
A WIDER INVESTIGATION INTO
ALLEGED TAX EVASION BY TOP
FOOTBALLERS.
HE WILL PAY A FINE OF 1.75
MILLION POUNDS.
POPE FRANCIS HAS ADMITTED FOR
THE FIRST TIME THAT CLERICS
SEXUALLY ABUSED NUNS.
HE SAID THAT THE CHURCH WAS
AWARE THAT PRIESTS AND BISHOPS
HAD ABUSED NUNS AND WAS WORKING
ON THE ISSUE.
POPE FRANCIS ADDED THAT HIS
PREDECESSOR POPE BENEDICT WAS
FORCED TO SHUT DOWN AN ENTIRE
CONGREGATION OF NUNS WHO WERE
BEING ABUSED BY PRIESTS.
POLICE IN PARIS SAID THAT THE
FIRE THAT ENGULFED THE
RESIDENTIAL BUILDING DURING THE
NIGHT, KILLING 10 PEOPLE, WAS
POSSIBLY STARTED ON PURPOSE.
THEY HAVE ARRESTED A WOMAN WHO
LIVED THERE.
AT LEAST 30 OTHER PEOPLE HAVE
BEEN INJURED IN THE BLAZE.
LUCY WILLIAMSON REPORTS FROM
PARIS.
LUCY: THE FIRE BRIGRADE
DESCRIBED IT AS APOCALYPTIC.
THE LIVING ROOMS, BEDROOMS,
HALLWAYS, FUEL FOR THE INFERNO.
TINY LADDERS HUNG FROM WINDOWS,
A LIFELINE ALLOWING FIREFIGHTERS
TO GET IN.
IT WAS A SCENE OF CHAOS.
THE SEARCH FOR RESIDENTS THROUGH
THE SMOKE-FILLED FLOORS
ACCOMPANIED BY THE SOUND OF
SCREAMING.
MANY SURVIVORS FOUND CLINGING TO
WINDOWSILLS OR ROOFS.
>> THE ALARM WENT OFF AFTER
MIDNIGHT, AND IT WAS ALREADY
BLACK WITH SMOKE.
I LIVE ON THE TOP FLOOR.
I HAD TO CLIMB SEVERAL BALCONIES
TO GET OUT.
WE HID IN THE CORNER WITH
SEVERAL PEOPLE TO ESCAPE THE
FLAMES.
LUCY: BY DAWN THE FIRE WAS UNDER
CONTROL.
BUT THE SEARCH FOR VICTIMS
CONTINUE.
WHEN FIREFIGHTERS ARRIVED THEY
FOUND THE BUILDING BEHIND A
COURTYARD WITH NO WAY OF
ACCESSING IT FROM THE STREET.
NORMAL LADDERS WERE USELESS.
THEY HAD TO USE SPECIAL
EQUIPMENT.
POLICE ARE TREATING IT AS ARSON
AND ARE QUESTIONING THE
-- QUESTIONING A RESIDENT.
>> A WOMAN WHO LIVES IN THE
BUILDING HAS BEEN QUESTIONED.
SHE IS 40 YEARS OLD AND HAS A
PREVIOUS HISTORY OF PSYCHIATRIC
DISORDERS.
LUCY: FIREFIGHTERS ARE WORKING
TO STABILIZE THE BUILDING AND
FIND THE SOURCE OF THE BLAZE.
THIS SEDATE CORNER OF PARIS NOW
A CRIME SCENE, A BARREN SHELL
BURNT BARE OF FAMILY LIFE.
LUCY WILLIAMSON, BBC NEWS,
PARIS.
LAURA: SO MANY QUESTIONS AFTER
THAT DEVASTATING FIRE IN PARIS.
YOU ARE WATCHING "BBC WORLD NEWS
AMERICA."
STILL TO COME ON TONIGHT'S
PROGRAM, IN BRAZIL, TALES OF
SURVIVAL AND DEVASTATING LOSS
FOLLOWING A MAJOR DAM COLLAPSE.
THE SEARCH FOR THE MISSING
CONTINUES.
THE U.K. MUSIC CHAIN WHICH
COLLAPSED IN DECEMBER, HAS BEEN
SAVED BY A CANADIAN RECORD
COMPANY.
IT WILL CLOSE THE FLAGSHIP STORE
IN CENTRAL LONDON.
THE NEW OWNER SAYS THEY WILL BE
LISTENING TO OTHER CUSTOMERS
WANT, INCLUDING A GREATER
SELECTION OF VINYL RECORDS.
>> LUNCHTIME, A QUICK STAMPEDE
TO THE RECORD SHOP.
REPORTER: FOR DECADES THEY HAVE
BEEN A HUGE PART OF LIFE FOR
MUSIC FANS AND FOR SOME OF
MUSIC'S BIGGEST ARTISTS.
NOW WHILE 100 STORES HAVE BEEN
SAVED, 27 ARE BEING SHUTDOWN,
INCLUDING THE ONE WHERE IT ALL
STARTED ALMOST 100 YEARS AGO ON
LONDON'S OXFORD STREET.
A PERHAPS INEVITABLE CONSEQUENCE
OF A MUSIC LOVING PUBLIC WHO
ENJOY SHOPPING AND PRESENT BUT
ALSO EMBRACED CONSUMING MUSIC
ONLINE.
>> PEOPLE ARE ORDERING ONLINE
AND STREAMING.
THERE IS STILL PEOPLE WHO WANT
TO COME AND BROWSE.
>> WE RELY ON THE OTHER THINGS
-- STREAMING MUSIC, WE STREAM TV
, STREAM FILMS.
THEY HAVE TO FIND A BUSINESS
MODEL SO THEY CAN SURVIVE.
REPORTER: ENTER THE OWNER OF
CANADIAN RETAILER SUNRISE
RECORDS, HMV'S NEW OWNERS.
>> WE TOOK OVER 80-SOME-ODD
STORES IN CANADA AND THEY ARE
DOING WELL, DOING STRONG,
PROFITABLE.
WE SEE HMV CONTINUING ON IN THE
U.K. FOR A LONG TIME.
REPORTER: WHAT CHALLENGES ARE
SIGNIFICANT.
HMV ONCE MADE ITS MONEY FROM
HUGE SALES OF CD'S AND GAMES,
ALL OF WHICH HAVE BEEN
PLUMMETING YEAR ON YEAR.
WHILE MANY STORES INCLUDING THE
FLAGSHIP ARE CLOSING, THEY ARE
SO CONFIDENT HMV CAN EXIST UP
AND DOWN THE COUNTRY TO THE
CENTENARY IN 2021 AND BEYOND.
LAURA: IN BRAZIL, THE SEARCH
CONTINUES FOR THOSE STILL
MISSING AFTER THE COLLAPSE OF A
MAJOR DAM.
THE DEATH TOLL STANDS AT 134
WITH NEARLY 200 OTHERS
UNACCOUNTED FOR.
OUR SOUTH AMERICAN CORRESPONDENT
KATY WATSON HAS BEEN TO THE SIDE
-- SITE OF THE DISASTER TO SPEAK
TO A WOMAN WHO LOST SIX MEMBERS
OF HER FAMILY AND TO A SURVIVOR
WHO HAD THE NARROWEST OF
ESCAPES.
KATY: WHEN THE DAM BROKE, THERE
WAS LITTLE HOPE FOR THOSE IN THE
PATH OF THE DELUGE THAT
FOLLOWED.
PANIC AS DRIVERS STRUGGLED TO
SAVE THEMSELVES.
HE WAS DRIVING ONE OF THE TRUCKS
THAT DAY.
"IT SOUNDED LIKE AN EXPLOSION,"
HE TELLS ME, BUT HE SOON
REALIZED WHAT HAPPENED.
>> WE SAW THE MUD COMING.
I TOLD MY FRIENDS, RUN, THE DAM
HAS BURST.
YOU CAN SEE ON THE VIDEO MY
TRUCK MOVING FROM ONE SIDE TO
THE OTHER.
THERE WAS NO WAY OUT.
WE ASKED GOD TO PROTECT US.
DEATH WAS STARING US IN THE
FACE.
KATY: THEY SURVIVED.
THIS WAS THE AFTERMATH.
HIS PICKUP WAS LIKE A GRAIN OF
SAND TOSSED IN THE CHAOS.
THIS MAN IS SEARCHING FOR THE
BODIES OF HIS BROTHER AND COUSIN
IN THE SLUDGE.
>> MY WORLD ENDED.
I KNEW I WOULDN'T FIND THEM
ALIVE HERE, BUT IF WE ARE NOT ON
TOP OF THE SEARCH, AUTHORITIES
WILL STOP LOOKING.
KATY: THE RECOVERY EFFORT IS
SLOW.
THERE HAS BEEN LOTS OF RAIN IN
THE LAST 24 HOURS, AND THE
FIREFIGHTERS ARE RETURNING TO
AREAS HOPING THAT WITH THE EXTRA
WATER IT MIGHT HAVE DISPLACED
THE MUD AND THEY CAN RECOVER
MORE BODIES.
EVERY SO OFTEN THEY FIND
SOMETHING.
A BODY BAG IS FLOWN BACK TO
WAITING FAMILIES.
THE EVENTS OF THIS PAST WEEK ARE
STILL HARD TO PROCESS FOR ELENA.
SHE WAS TO BECOME A GRANDMOTHER.
WHEN THE DAM COLLAPSED, THAT
DREAM ENDED.
HER DAUGHTER, SON, AND PREGNANT
DAUGHTER-IN-LAW WERE KILLED WHEN
A WALL OF SLUDGE SLAMMED INTO
THE HOTEL THEY WERE STAYING IN.
HER EX-HUSBAND AND HIS WIFE DIED
WITH THEM.
ELENA SPELLS OUT THEIR INITIALS.
>> AND THEY WERE THROWN I DON'T
KNOW WHERE.
THEY DIED FROM CRANIAL TRAUMA.
THAT WAS THE CORONER'S VERDICT.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT WAS A SLOW OR
QUICK DEATH.
KATY: THE FAMILY'S MOURNING IS
ALL THE HARDER BECAUSE THEY HAVE
NOT FOUND ALL THE BODIES YET.
IN THE DISTANCE, THE SEARCH GOES
ON.
KATY WATSON, BBC NEWS.
LAURA: SO MUCH LOSS AND GRIEF IN
BRAZIL.
DON MCCULLIN HAS TRAINED HIS
CAMERA LENS ON IMAGES OF WAR
AROUND THE WORLD.
HIS IMAGES FROM VIETNAM ONE HIM
AWARDS AND RESPECT IN EQUAL
MEASURE.
EVEN THOUGH HE IS NOW IN HIS
80'S, THE PHOTOGRAPHER HAS BEEN
TO SYRIA AND YEMEN.
HE HAS ALSO PHOTOGRAPHED
INEQUALITY IN HIS NATIVE
BRITAIN.
HIS CLASSIC IMAGES ARE ON
DISPLAY IN LONDON.
REPORTER: LIFE AND DEATH, AS
CAPTURED BY DON MCCULLIN.
DON: EVERYTHING ABOUT ME HAS
BEEN VERY INSTINCTIVE.
KNOWING THAT I SHOULD BE IN THIS
SPACE AND THAT PLACE.
REPORTER: THIS EXHIBITION BRINGS
TOGETHER MORE THAN 250
PHOTOGRAPHS BY ONE OF THE
WORLD'S GREATEST PHOTOGRAPHERS.
DON: THIS PHOTOGRAPH IS YOU
COULD SAY THE BEGINNING OF MY
WHOLE LIFE'S WORK.
I STARTED PHOTOGRAPHING THE
LOCAL BOYS WHO USED TO HANG OUT
AND NONE OF US WERE GOING
ANYWHERE IN LIFE.
THIS PHOTOGRAPH IS THE VERY
FIRST PICTURE I TOOK OF THE WAR.
REPORTER: CYPRIOT CIVIL WAR OF
1964.
DON: LOOKS LIKE A STILL FROM
SOME MAFIOSO FILM.
REPORTER: WERE YOU SCARED?
DON: NO, I WAS TOO EXCITED TO BE
SCARED.
I WAS SCARED OF NOT GETTING
PICTURES.
HIS REPUTATION GROWING RAPIDLY,
DON MCCULLIN'S ASSIGNMENTS TOOK
INTO WAR ZONES ACROSS THE WORLD.
DON: THAT WAS IN CAMBODIA.
REPORTER: WHAT MAKES A GREAT
PHOTOGRAPH AS FAR AS YOU ARE
CONCERNED?
DON: IT HAS IMPACT.
I DO NOT WANT YOU TO WALK PAST
MY PICTURES WITHOUT GETTING SOME
MESSAGE FROM IT.
REPORTER: AS WELL AS WARZONES
FAR AWAY, DON MCCULLIN HAS ALSO
FOCUSED ON CONFLICT AND
DEPRIVATION CLOSE TO HOME.
THESE PICTURES ARE BLACK AND
WHITE.
WHY IS THAT?
DON: BLACK AND WHITE HAS A MUCH
STRONGER WAY OF VOICING ITSELF
TO YOU.
IT IS A SILENT VOICE, BUT I
WANTED TO BE A SHOUTING SILENT
VOICE SO YOU DON'T MISS IT.
REPORTER: SOME PHOTOGRAPHERS
HAVE BEMOANED THE UBIQUITY OF
CAMERA PHONES.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DON: PEOPLE ARE REALIZING THEY
WANT TO RECORD THEIR LIVES.
IN A WAY IT IS ENHANCING THE
LOVE OF PHOTOGRAPHY.
I WENT TO VIETNAM, BUT IT WAS
NOT UNTIL 1968 THAT I CAME
ACROSS A REAL OPPORTUNITY TO
STAY IN A BATTLE FOR NEARLY TWO
WEEKS.
THIS PICTURE, I CALL IT MY
CRUCIFIXION.
I SAID TO ONE OF THE SOLDIERS,
LOOK AFTER THESE.
I WAS 31 YEARS OLD AND STRONG AS
A LION.
I COULD DO IT.
REPORTER: THIS IMAGE CAPTURED
POST-TRAUMATIC STRESS DISORDER
LONG BEFORE THE CONDITION WAS
OFFICIALLY ACKNOWLEDGED.
DON: HE WAS SHELLSHOCKED, AND
MARINES DON'T RESPECT PEOPLE WHO
DON'T FIGHT.
THEY WERE TREATING HIM VERY
SHABBILY, REALLY.
EVERYTHING I HAVE DONE IN THIS
ROOM IS NOT GOING TO CHANGE THE
WORLD.
IT IS JUST AN ATTEMPT TO SHOW
PEOPLE THAT IT IS WRONG, THAT'S
ALL.
LAURA: DON MCCULLIN'S IMAGES OF
WAR.
BEFORE WE GO, WE WANT TO WISH
EVERYONE A HEALTHY AND
PROSPEROUS YEAR OF THE PIG.
IT IS CHINA'S NEW YEAR.
THE STATE BROADCASTER PUT ON THE
ANNUAL CAP AGAINST THE.
AN ESTIMATED 700 MILLION PEOPLE
TUNED INTO THE EVENT EVERY
SINGLE YEAR.
IT IS MARKED BY FIREWORKS AND
DANCING AND THE EXCHANGE OF
PACKETS FILLED WITH MONEY FOR
THE HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE HIT THE
ROAD TO MEET WITH LOVED ONES,
MAKING IT THE LARGEST ANIMAL
MIGRATION IN THE WORLD.
HAPPY YEAR OF THE PIG.
I AM LAURA TREVELYAN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR WATCHING
"BBC WORLD NEWS AMERICA."
>> WITH THE BBC NEWS APP, OUR
VERTICAL VIDEOS ARE DESIGNED TO
WORK AROUND YOUR LIFESTYLE, SO
YOU CAN SWIPE YOUR WAY THROUGH
THE NEWS OF THE DAY AND STAY
UP-TO-DATE WITH THE LATEST
HEADLINES YOU CAN TRUST.
DOWNLOAD NOW FROM SELECTED APP
STORES.
>> FUNDING OF THIS PRESENTATION
IS MADE POSSIBLE BY
THE FREEMAN FOUNDATION,
AND KOVLER FOUNDATION, PURSUING
SOLUTIONS FOR AMERICA'S
NEGLECTED NEEDS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> A NEW .
>> NOW YOU CAN ACCESS MORE OF
YOUR FAVORITE PBS SHOWS THAN
EVER BEFORE,
WITH PBS PASSPORT, A MEMBER
BENEFIT THAT LETS YOU BINGE MANY
OF THE LATEST SHOWS AND CATCH UP
ON YOUR FAVORITES.
>> WE REALLY ARE LIVING IN THE
MODERN WORLD.
>> ANYTIME YOU WANT.
>> WOW, HOW ABOUT THAT?
>> ANYWHERE YOU ARE.
>> THERE IS LITERALLY NOTHING
LIKE THIS IN THE WORLD.
>> SUPPORT YOUR PBS STATION AND
GET PASSPORT.
YOUR TICKET TO THE BEST OF PBS.
>> "BBC WORLD NEWS" WAS
PRESENTED BY KCET, LOS ANGELES.
>> Announcer: THIS