>> THIS IS "BBC WORLD NEWS
AMERICA."
FUNDING OF THIS PRESENTATION IS
MADE POSSIBLE BY
THE FREEMAN FOUNDATION,
AND KOVLER FOUNDATION, PURSUING
SOLUTIONS FOR AMERICA'S
NEGLECTED NEEDS.
>> WOW, THAT IS UNBELIEVABLE.
♪
>> I'M FLYING!
>> STAY CURIOUS.
♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> AND NOW, "BBC WORLD NEWS."
JANE: THIS IS "BBC WORLD NEWS
AMERICA."
REPORTING FROM WASHINGTON, I AM
JANE O'BRIEN.
CONGRESSIONAL DEMOCRATS ANNOUNCE
NEW INVESTIGATIONS INTO
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HE SAYS IT IS HARASSMENT.
REVEALING THE DARK SIDE OF
BRAZIL'S MINING INDUSTRY.
TOXIC WASTE IS BEING HELD BACK
BY DAMS THAT HAVE THE POTENTIAL
TO COLLAPSE.
>> IF THE WHOLE LOT BRAKES, ALL
THESE TOXINS COULD ENTER THE
WATER SUPPLY OF MILLIONS OF
PEOPLE.
JANE: BEHOLD THE ROVER.
SOON IT WILL BE HEADING TO MARS
BEARING THE NAME OF A
GROUNDBREAKING SCIENTIST.
JANE: WELCOME TO OUR VIEWERS ON
PUBLIC TELEVISION IN AMERICA AND
AROUND THE GLOBE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS BRACING
HIMSELF FOR A NEW WAVE OF
INVESTIGATIONS AFTER A WARNING
IN HIS STATE OF THE UNION SPEECH
THAT SUCH MOVES WOULD ONLY HARM
THE NATION.
DEMOCRATS ON KEY OVERSIGHT
COMMITTEES SAY THEY WILL DEMAND
HIS TAX RETURNS AS PART OF
BROADER INQUIRIES INTO HIS
BUSINESS DEALINGS.
THEY ARE ALSO REOPENING AN
INVESTIGATION INTO RUSSIAN
ELECTION MEDDLING AND POSSIBLE
COLLUSION BY THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN.
NOT SURPRISINGLY, THE PRESIDENT
IS FURIOUS.
TODAY HE TWEETED, "PRESIDENTIAL
HARASSMENT.
IT SHOULD NEVER BE ALLOWED TO
HAPPEN AGAIN."
I SPOKE A SHORT TIME AGO TO
SHANNON PETTYPIECE OF BLOOMBERG.
THERE ARE SO MANY
INVESTIGATIONS.
WHAT ARE THESE NEW
INVESTIGATIONS LOOKING FOR AND
WHAT MIGHT THEY FIND?
SHANNON: THERE ARE SO MANY, AND
THEY ARE SO BROAD AT THIS POINT.
THE DEMOCRATS HAVE NOT NARROWED
IT DOWN THE EXACT AREAS THEY
WILL PROBE.
THEY HAVE TALKED ABOUT
EVERYTHING FROM THE PRESIDENT'S
HOTEL IN WASHINGTON AND WHETHER
IT VIOLATES THE CONSTITUTION,
THEY HAVE TALKED ABOUT THE TAX
RETURNS, AS YOU MENTIONED, HIS
CONNECTIONS TO RUSSIA, HIS
INDIVIDUAL BUSINESS DEALINGS --
HIS HOTELS IN NEW YORK, PANAMA,
PROJECTS IN CANADA.
TO GO DEEP INTO HIS BUSINESS,
HIS PERSONAL FINANCES, INTO HIS
ADMINISTRATION.
AND THEN THERE IS ALL THE THINGS
THAT HAPPENED WHILE HE IS
PRESIDENT -- SECURITY
CLEARANCES, DEALINGS BY CABINET
SECRETARIES.
YES, IT COULD BE VERY BROAD.
THE DEMOCRATS HAVE NOT NAILED
DOWN THE FOCUS AND THEY HAVE TO
DO THAT IN THE NEXT MONTH OR SO
BECAUSE THEY HAVE LIMITED
RESOURCES.
JANE: HOW IS THIS GOING TO
AFFECT THE WORKINGS OF THE WHITE
HOUSE?
SHANNON: IT COULD REALLY DRAG A
LOT OF THE ADMINISTRATION TO A
HALT.
WHEN YOU TALK TO PAST WHITE
HOUSES -- THE CLINTON WHITE
HOUSE IS THE BEST PARALLEL TO
THIS -- THE CONSTANT DRUMBEAT OF
INVESTIGATIONS -- YOU HAVE THE
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL'S OFFICE
DEALING WITH A RESPONSE TO THE
SUBPOENAS.
PEOPLE WITH THE CLINTON
ADMINISTRATION TOLD ME THERE
BECOMES A GENERAL ANXIETY AND
CONCERN IN THE WHITE HOUSE -- AM
I GOING TO GET SUBPOENAED, THE
STAFFERS START THINKING.
THEY WORRY WHAT THEY SAID TO
SOMEONE AND WHAT RECORDS WERE
KEPT.
AS FAR AS THE NEWS CYCLE GOES
THERE WILL BE A DAILY DRUMBEAT
OF SUBPOENAS, TESTIMONIES, NEW
DOCUMENTS, AND THAT WILL
DISTRACT FROM THE AGENDA OF
OTHER THINGS THEY WOULD LIKE TO
GET DONE AND BE TALKING ABOUT.
JANE: PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS WARNED
IN THE PAST THAT IF THE
INVESTIGATIONS CROSSED A RED
LINE, HE MIGHT DO SOMETHING
ABOUT IT.
WHAT CAN HE DO?
SHANNON: WHEN IT COMES TO
CONGRESS, NOT THAT MUCH.
THAT IS WHY THIS SORT OF MAKES
THE ROBERT MUELLER INVESTIGATION
LOOK LIKE A WARMUP ROUND.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT CONGRESS,
SEPARATE BRANCH OF GOVERNMENT,
AND THE ABILITY IT HAS AND THE
LARGE SUBPOENA POWER IT HAS,
THERE IS NOT MUCH HE CAN DO.
HE CAN FIGHT BACK INSIDE -- HE
CAN FIGHT BACK AND CITE
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE ON SOME
THINGS AND PUSH BACK ON
SUBPOENAS, SAYING THAT THEY ARE
IRRELEVANT, YOU ARE GOING AFTER
PRIVATE COMPANIES.
BUT CONGRESS DOES HAVE HER BROAD
INVESTIGATIVE POWERS.
HE HAS SEPARATE INVESTIGATIONS
TO WORRY ABOUT -- NEW YORK IN
THE SOUTHERN DISTRICT, OUTSIDE
OF HIS CONTROL, CONTINUING TO
PURSUE THINGS WITH HIS INAUGURAL
COMMITTEE, THE LATEST EXAMPLE OF
SOMEPLACE THEY HAVE BEEN LOOKING
AT.
JANE: HE HAS ALREADY TWEETED.
HOW ELSE MIGHT HE REACT?
SHANNON: THE TWEET IS
INTERESTING BECAUSE HE IS
STARTING TO PICK A FIGHT BEFORE
THE FIGHT HAS BEGUN, SOMETHING
HE TENDS TO DO.
YES, THE DEMOCRATS HAVE TALKED
BROADLY ABOUT WHAT THEY WANT TO
INVESTIGATE, BUT IT IS NOT LIKE
50 SUBPOENAS HAVE LANDED IN THE
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL'S OFFICE,
NOT LIKE THEY HAD DEMANDED HIS
SON COME IN FOR A PUBLIC
HEARING.
THERE IS POTENTIAL FOR ALL OF
THAT TO HAPPEN, BUT HE HAS GONE
OUT AHEAD.
WHAT THAT DOES IS POKE THE BEAR.
IT GOES AFTER THE COMMITTEES AND
RLES THEM UP, AND SOME MEMBERS
FEEL LIKE THEY HAVE TO
INVESTIGATE JUST TO SHOW THEM
-- HIM THAT THEY HAVE THAT POWER
AND THAT ABILITY TO DO SO.
JANE: SHANNON PETTYPIECE, THANKS
VERY MUCH INDEED FOR JOINING ME.
THE POLITICAL CRISIS IN VIRGINIA
IS DEEPENING AMID ALLEGATIONS OF
RACIAL AND SEXUAL MISCONDUCT BY
THE STATE'S LEADERS.
THE THREE TOP DEMOCRATS ARE IN
HOT WATER, BUT SO FAR THERE ARE
NO SIGNS THEY ARE STEPPING DOWN,
AND THE STORY DOESN'T END THERE.
THE IMAGES IN THE 1968 YEARBOOK
OF THE PRESTIGIOUS VIRGINIA
MILITARY INSTITUTE ARE SHOCKING.
IT HAS BEEN REPORTED THAT THE
-- THAT TOMMY NORMENT, THE STATE
SENATE MAJORITY LEADER, WAS THE
EDITOR AT THE TIME.
HE HAS DISTANCED HIMSELF, SAYING
HE DID NOT OVERSEE EVERY PAGE OF
THE PUBLICATION.
MEANWHILE, TWO OF HER VIRGINIA'S
TOP THREE DEMOCRATS HAVE
ADMITTED TO PAST RACIST
BEHAVIOR, AND THE LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR IS ACCUSED OF SEXUAL
ASSAULT.
JUSTIN FAIRFAX DENIES THE
ALLEGATIONS, BUT HIS ACCUSER,
VANESSA TYSON, HAS GIVEN NEW
DETAILS OF THE ENCOUNTER IN
2004.
IN A STATEMENT, SHE SAID,
"CONSENSUAL KISSING QUICKLY
TURNED INTO A SEXUAL ASSAULT."
FAIRFAX DESCRIBED HER ACCOUNT AS
PAINFUL, BUT SAID, "I HAVE NEVER
DONE ANYTHING LIKE WHAT SHE
SUGGESTS."
NATIONAL DEMOCRATS HAVE ADOPTED
ZERO-TOLERANCE OF MEN ACCUSED OF
SEXUAL MISCONDUCT.
THEY HAVE CALLED FOR AN
INVESTIGATION OF THE
ALLEGATIONS, BUT FEW HAVE
DEMANDED FURTHER ACTION YET.
>> THIS HAS BEEN AN AWFUL WEEK
FOR VIRGINIA.
JANE: GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM,
WHOSE COLLEGE YEARBOOK PHOTO
STARTED THE CRISIS, IS REFUSING
TO RESIGN.
STATE ATTORNEY GENERAL MARK
HERRING, WHO ADMITTED WEARING
BLACKFACE AT A PARTY IN THE
1980'S, IS ALSO STAYING PUT FOR
NOW.
VIRGINIA IS A KEY POLITICAL
BATTLEGROUND, BUT THE CRISIS
THREATENS TO WEAKEN DEMOCRATS
AHEAD OF STATE ELECTIONS IN
NOVEMBER AND NEXT YEAR'S
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION, WHEN THEY
WILL TRY TO DRAW A BRIGHT LINE
BETWEEN THEIR CANDIDATE AND
DONALD TRUMP.
FOR MORE ON THE UPHEAVAL IN THE
STATE, MY COLLEAGUES KATTY KAY
AND CHRISTIAN FRASER SPOKE TO
LARRY SABATO, DIRECTOR OF THE
CENTER OF POLITICS AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA, AND THEY
STARTED BY ASKING HIM ABOUT THE
CURRENT LEVEL OF CHAOS.
LARRY: WHAT IS HAPPENING HERE IS
THAT THE ENTIRE ELECTED
SUPERSTRUCTURE OF THE STATE IS
NOW INVOLVED IN VARIOUS
SCANDALS, AND WE JUST ADDED ONE.
THE REPUBLICAN MAJORITY LEADER
OF THE STATE SENATE.
SO IT IS NOW OFFICIALLY A
BIPARTISAN SCANDAL.
CHRISTIAN: AS I UNDERSTAND IT,
LARRY, IF ALL THESE THREE
DEMOCRATS WERE TO STEP DOWN, THE
NEXT IN LINE TO BECOME GOVERNOR
WOULD BE THE HOUSE SPEAKER, WHO
IS A REPUBLICAN.
LARRY: THAT IS RIGHT, AND THAT
IS WHY IT WON'T HAPPEN.
THE PEOPLE OF VIRGINIA VOTED
OVERWHELMINGLY, REALLY IN
LANDSLIDE PROPORTIONS, FOR
DEMOCRATS IN 2017, AND THAT WAS
TRUE FOR ALL THREE OF THEM.
THAT WON'T HAPPEN BECAUSE IT IS
CONTRARY TO THE POPULAR WILL AND
IT WOULD BE SEEN AS A KIND OF
SILENT COUP.
THE PEOPLE WHO INSTIGATED SOME
OF THESE CHARGES ARE CLEARLY
CONNECTED TO THE REPUBLICAN
PARTY AND SOME VERY CONSERVATIVE
WEBSITES.
SO IT IS JUST NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN.
THEY WILL FIND SOME WAY TO
STAGGER RESIGNATIONS, IF IT EVEN
COMES TO RESIGNATION, SO THAT A
DEMOCRAT WILL SUCCEED TO THE
GOVERNORSHIP, A DEMOCRAT WHO CAN
STAY THERE.
KATTY: LARRY, I WANT TO ASK YOU
ABOUT JUSTIN FAIRFAX IN A
SECOND, BUT FIRST OF ALL, THIS
ISSUE OF RACE AND VIRGINIA AND
TO WHAT EXTENT THE ACCUSATIONS
AGAINST THE TWO DEMOCRATS WHO
HAVE BEEN ACCUSED OF BLACKENING
THEIR FACES, TO WHAT EXTENT IS
THAT REPRESENTATIVE OF
VIRGINIA'S FAIRLY RECENT RACIAL
PAST?
LARRY: I THINK IT IS ALL TOO
REPRESENTATIVE, TO BE BLUNT
ABOUT IT.
I WAS BORN IN THIS STATE AND
GREW UP ABOUT A DECADE PRIOR TO
THE TWO DEMOCRATS WHO ARE IN
TROUBLE RIGHT NOW FOR BLACKFACE.
I HATE TO ADMIT IT, BUT EVEN AT
MY OWN UNIVERSITY THERE HAVE
BEEN SUBSTANTIAL INCIDENTS OF
BLACKFACE OVER THE YEARS, AND
IN FACT, ONE OF THE DEMOCRATS
WHO IS IN TROUBLE BECAUSE OF
BLACKFACE USED IT AS AN
UNDERGRADUATE STUDENT AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA.
SO IT IS NOT JUST HERE, IT IS
EVERYWHERE.
WE ARE FINDING PHOTOS IN A JUST
ABOUT ALL OF THE COLLEGE
YEARBOOKS.
SO THIS IS A PROBLEM THAT
PROBABLY IS GENERIC IN THE
SOUTH, BUT RIGHT NOW THE FOCUS
IS ON VIRGINIA, AND IT POINTS
UP THE VERY DIFFICULT
RELATIONSHIP WE'VE HAD AMONG THE
RACES IN VIRGINIA, AND EVEN
THOUGH WE HAVE MADE PROGRESS, WE
HAVE PROBABLY MADE LESS PROGRESS
THAN WE THINK.
KATTY: OK, SO IF THE
RELATIONSHIPS BETWEEN RACES WERE
NOT TRICKY ENOUGH, THIS STORY IS
ALSO HIGHLIGHTING THE
RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN GENDERS AS
WELL, BECAUSE THE NUMBER TWO
DEMOCRAT, AN AFRICAN-AMERICAN,
HAS BEEN ACCUSED OF HARASSMENT.
I WANT TO READ WHAT HIS ACCUSER,
VANESSA TYSON, SAID, "WHAT
STARTED AS CONSENSUAL KISSING
QUICKLY TURNED INTO SEXUAL
ASSAULT."
SHOULD GOES ON TO -- SHE GOES ON
TO GIVE A GRAPHIC ACCOUNT OF
BEING FORCED TO PERFORM ORAL SEX
ON JUSTIN FAIRFAX.
HE DENIES IT AND SAID, "I TAKE
THIS SITUATION SERIOUSLY AND
CONTINUE TO BELIEVE DR. TYSON
SHOULD BE TREATED WITH RESPECT,
BUT I CANNOT AGREE WITH A
DESCRIPTION OF EVENTS THAT IS
SIMPLY NOT TRUE."
WHERE DOES THIS LEAVE NUMBER TWO
DEMOCRAT JUSTIN FAIRFAX?
IN THE ERA OF ME TOO, LARRY, IN
THE POST-BRETT KAVANAUGH PERIOD,
WHERE DOES THIS LEAVE HIM?
LARRY: IT LEAVES HIM IN DEEP
TROUBLE AND DAMAGED FOR THE
FUTURE, EVEN IF THIS CANNOT BE
PROVEN ONE WAY OR THE OTHER, AND
IT PROBABLY CAN'T.
THIS WAS 2004 AND THERE WERE NO
TEMPORARY WITNESSES -- NO
CONTEMPORARY WITNESSES OR
CONTEMPORANEOUS TESTIMONY.
ALTHOUGH THE SENIOR
AFRICAN-AMERICAN OFFICEHOLDER IN
VIRGINIA, CONGRESSMAN BOBBY
SCOTT, TODAY HE SAID HE KNEW
SOME OF IT WAS TRUE.
HE HAD DATED THIS WOMAN A COUPLE
OF YEARS AGO AND HAD HEARD THE
ACCOUNT THEN.
SO LESS THAN A WEEK AGO, THIS
AFRICAN-AMERICAN NUMBER TWO IN
VIRGINIA WAS ON THE VERGE OF
TAKING THE OATH OF OFFICE AS
GOVERNOR.
NOW HE IS GOING TO BE VERY LUCKY
TO FINISH HIS TERM AS LIEUTENANT
GOVERNOR, AND HIS FUTURE IS
CLOUDY.
JANE: LARRY SABATO FROM THE
UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA.
A LOOK AT SOME OF THE DAY'S
OTHER NEWS.
THE UNITED NATIONS INQUIRY INTO
THE MURDER  OF JOURNALIST
JAMAL KHASHOGGI SAID HE WAS THE
VICTIM OF A BRUTAL AND
PREMEDITATED KILLING CARRIED OUT
BY SAUDI ARABIAN STATE
OFFICIALS.
IT ACCUSES SAUDI ARABIA OF
UNDERMINING EFFORTS TO
INVESTIGATE THE MURDER WHICH
TOOK PLACE IN THE SAUDI
CONSULATE IN ISTANBUL.
THE HEAD OF THE SOCIAL-MEDIA
PLATFORM INSTAGRAM HAS PLEDGED
TO REMOVE ALL GRAPHIC IMAGES OF
SELF HARM.
THE PROMISE MADE TO THE BBC
COMES AFTER THE FATHER OF A
14-YEAR-OLD BRITISH GIRL WHO
TOOK HER OWN LIFE ASSERTED THAT
INSTAGRAM HELPED KILL HIS
DAUGHTER.
THE HOSPITAL TREATING BRAZILIAN
PRESIDENT JAIR BOLSONARO SAYS HE
IS SUFFERING FROM PNEUMONIA.
MR. BOLSONARO NEARLY DIED AFTER
BEING STABBED IN THE ABDOMEN
DURING THE PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION
CAMPAIGN LAST YEAR.
HE HAS BEEN IN HOSPITAL FOR THE
PAST 12 DAYS AFTER A SECOND
ROUND OF SURGERY.
IT IS NOT CLEAR WHEN HE WILL BE
WELL ENOUGH TO BE DISCHARGED.
BRAZIL SUFFERED ONE OF THE
COUNTRY'S WORST-EVER
ENVIRONMENTAL DISASTERS LAST
MONTH WHEN A DAM AT A MINE
COLLAPSED, FLOODING THE AREA
WITH SLUDGE.
NEARLY 150 ARE KNOWN TO HAVE
DIED, WITH MANY MORE STILL
MISSING.
MUCH OF THE ATTENTION HAS
FOCUSED ON THE MINE OWNERS, VALE
, AND THE POOR SAFETY STANDARDS.
BUT SOME BLAME THE POWERFUL
MINING INDUSTRY AS A WHOLE AND
INADEQUATE GOVERNMENT
REGULATION.
FOR THIS REPORT, THE BBC'S
SCIENCE EDITOR DAVID SHUKMAN
WENT TO A TOWN NOT FAR FROM THE
DISASTER SCENE.
DAVID: WE TRAVELED TO THE HEART
OF BRAZIL'S IRON COUNTRY TO
INVESTIGATE THE DARK SIDE OF THE
MINES THAT THE INDUSTRY PREFERS
TO KEEP HIDDEN.
WE COME ACROSS A LURIDLY COLORED
STREAM, A FIRST CLUE ABOUT THE
POLLUTION CREATED IN THESE
HILLS.
SUDDENLY WE GET THIS RARE
GLIMPSE OF ONE OF THE LARGEST
MINING DUMPS IN BRAZIL.
IT IS FULL OF THE SAME KIND OF
SLUDGE THAT FLOODED OUT AND
KILLED SO MANY PEOPLE, A
BYPRODUCT THAT ACCUMULATES DAY
AFTER DAY FROM A MASSIVE
BUSINESS.
THE REASON THESE PLACES EXIST IS
WHEN YOU DIG OR OUT OF THE
GROUND, YOU ONLY WANT A TINY
FRACTION OF THE ROCK, THE METAL
THAT YOU ARE AFTER -- IN THIS
CASE, IRON.
THE REST YOU HAVE JUST GOT TO
GET RID OF, AND THE CHEAPEST WAY
TO DO THAT IS TO BUILD PLACES
LIKE THIS.
THE PROBLEM IS THEY ARE NOT
TEMPORARY.
THEY ARE MEANT TO LAST FOREVER.
THIS TOWERING STRUCTURE HOLDS
THE SLUDGE BACK, A DAM MADE OF
LAYERS OF MINING WASTE.
THERE ARE NEARLY 800 OF THESE IN
BRAZIL, AND MANY SAY THEY ARE
FAR TOO WEAK.
PEOPLE LIVING IN THE SHADOW OF
THE BARRIER HAVE CREATED THIS
COMPUTER SIMULATION OF HOW THEIR
HOMES COULD BE OVERWHELMED.
WHEN THE DAM DISINTEGRATED LAST
MONTH, IT LEFT OF THEM MORE
SCARED THAN EVER.
>> I DON'T SLEEP ANYMORE SINCE
WHAT HAPPENED.
IT WAS A WARNING.
IF THE SAME WERE TO HAPPEN HERE,
IN THREE YEARS, LESS THAN THREE
YEARS, TOMORROW, LATER, I DON'T
KNOW.
THE FEAR IS CONSTANT.
DAVID: NO CAMERA, NO VIDEO, NO
MONITORING.
NOT FAR AWAY, CAMPAIGNERS LEAD
ME TO ANOTHER SOURCE OF FEAR, AN
OLD GOLD LINE THAT HAS BEEN
-- AN OLD GOLD MINE THAT HAS
BEEN ABANDONED.
THE MACHINERY IS RUSTING.
THERE ARE POOLS OF LIQUID.
YOU GET ARSENIC AND CYANIDE WITH
GOLD-MINING.
IT IS MUCH MORE TOXIC THAN
MINING IRON ORE, AND THE WASTE
IS FAR MORE DANGEROUS.
THE LAST OWNERS OF THE MINE LEFT
A LEGACY THAT IS POISONOUS, A
MOUNTAIN OF CONTAMINATED DUST
AND ROCK, AND THE IMPACT OF ALL
OF THIS BEING RELEASED WOULD
BE DEVASTATING.
WHAT IS TRULY SHOCKING ABOUT
THIS PLACE IS THAT YOU HAVE THIS
HUGE LOAD OF HIGHLY TOXIC WASTE
HELD BACK BY A DAM I AM STANDING
ON THAT LITERALLY NO ONE IS
MAINTAINING.
RIGHT BESIDE IT, THIS LAKE OF
HIGHLY TOXIC LIQUID, ALSO HELD
BACK BY A DAM NO ONE IS LOOKING
AFTER.
IF THE WHOLE LOT BREAKS, ALL OF
THESE TOXINS COULD ENTER THE
WATER SUPPLY FOR MILLIONS OF
PEOPLE.
THE MINE IS IN AN AREA THAT IS A
VITAL SOURCE OF WATER.
A MAJOR CITY DEPENDS ON IT.
>> IF A VERY HEAVY RAIN FALLS,
WHO IS GOING TO GUARANTEE THAT
THIS DAM WON'T COLLAPSE?
IT IS REALLY SERIOUS.
DAVID: SO, DOWNSTREAM THERE IS A
RISK OF THE WATER BECOMING
TOXIC.
THIS SCIENTIST SAYS THE BROKEN
DAM HIGHLIGHTED WHAT COULD GO
WRONG.
>> I KNOW THE IMPORTANCE OF THE
WATER IN THIS PLACE FOR ALL THE
PEOPLE.
ALL THE CITIES AROUND THE MINE.
DAVID: BACK AT THE GOLD MINE, A
PITIFUL SIGHT, EMACIATED HORSES.
LIKE THE DAM, IT SEEMS NO ONE
CARES FOR THEM.
THERE ARE IDEAS FOR MAKING THESE
PLACES SAFE, BUT THERE ARE SO
MANY OF THEM, WHICH MEANS MORE
DISASTERS ARE WAITING TO HAPPEN.
DAVID SHUKMAN, BBC NEWS, IN
BRAZIL.
JANE: YOU ARE WATCHING "BBC
WORLD NEWS AMERICA."
STILL TO COME ON TONIGHT'S
PROGRAM, THE BRITISH PUBLIC HAS
SPOKEN.
THE NAME OF THE NEW MARS ROVER
WILL HONOR SCIENTIST ROSALIND
FRANKLIN.
20,000 DEAD OR DYING BIRDS HAVE
BEEN WASHED UP ON BEACHES ALONG
THE DUTCH COAST.
THEY ALL SHOWED SIGNS OF SEVERE
STARVATION.
SOME FEAR THERE WAS -- THAT IS
STILL FOR MUCH OF LAST MONTH
CAUSED THE DEATHS.
SOME OF THEM MAY HAVE BEEN
TRANSPORTING HAZARDOUS
MATERIALS.
A WARNING, YOU MAY FIND SOME OF
THESE IMAGES DISTRESSING.
REPORTER: THIS IS JUST ONE OF
THOUSANDS WASHED UP ON THE
BEACHES.
THE MASSIVE DEATHS HERE ON THE
DUTCH COAST HAVE BAFFLED
SCIENTISTS WHO ARE PURSUING
THREE MAIN LINES OF INQUIRY --
THE BIRDS MAY HAVE EATEN PLASTIC
, THEY COULD HAVE BEEN POISONED
BY CARAVAN LEAKING INTO THE SEA,
OR THAT HAZARDOUS CHEMICALS MAY
HAVE SOAKED INTO THEIR FEATHERS
FROM AFFECTING THEIR ABILITY TO
HUNT AND INSULATE THEMSELVES
FROM THE WATER.
A BIOLOGIST AND SEABIRD
SPECIALIST IS LEADING THE
INVESTIGATION.
>> YOUNG AND IN VERY BAD SHAPE.
EVEN ON THE OUTSIDE IT IS REALLY
SKINNY.
REPORTER: THE BIRDS FEED MOSTLY
ON FISH.
THE SEA IS RICH IN BASS AND
HERRING.
FOOD SHORTAGES ARE UNLIKELY.
BAD WEATHER MAY HAVE
CONTRIBUTED, BUT THAT DOES NOT
EXPLAIN WHY THE DEATHS ARE
LIMITED TO THE NETHERLANDS AND'S
POPULATION.
-- AND THIS PREPARATION.
>> IF IT IS INGESTED, IT SHOULD
STILL BE IN THE STOMACH BECAUSE
IT DOESN'T DIGEST.
REPORTER: THE SCIENTISTS HOPE
THAT MASS POSTMORTEMS ON THE
BIRDS WILL REVEAL WHAT IS
CAUSING THE DEATHS BEYOND ANY
REASONABLE DOUBT.
JANE: INTERNATIONAL PRESSURE IS
MOUNTING ON NICOLAS MADURO AS
THE CRISIS IN VENEZUELA
CONTINUES.
LEADERS FROM EUROPE AND LATIN
AMERICA HAVE SAID IT IS CRUCIAL
TO RESTORE DEMOCRACY AFTER
DISPUTED ELECTIONS RESULTED IN
JUAN GUAIDO DECLARING HIMSELF
INTERIM PRESIDENT.
AS THE POWER STRUGGLE PLAYS OUT
THERE, IT IS CLEAR MANY ORDINARY
VENEZUELANS ARE STRUGGLING TO
GET BY.
OUR CORRESPONDENT JAMES REYNOLDS
TOOK A RIDE ON A BUS THROUGH THE
CAPITAL, CARACAS, TO FIND OUT
HOW THEY ARE TRYING TO COPE.
JANE: JAMES REYNOLDS TALKING TO
VENEZUELANS ON A BUS ABOUT THE
CRISIS IN CARACAS.
SHE WAS A PIONEER IN SCIENCE,
AND THE NEW MARS ROVER WILL BEAR
THE NAME OF ROSALIND FRANKLIN.
OVER 30,000 PEOPLE ACROSS EUROPE
TOOK PART IN THE NAMING
COMPETITION, AND THE CHOSEN NAME
WAS UNVEILED EARLIER TODAY.
REBECCA MORELLE WAS THERE AND
SHE SENT THIS REPORT.
REBECCA: I AM HERE WHERE THIS
PROTOTYPE ROVER HEADS BEEN PUT
THROUGH ITS PACES.
IT IS DESIGNED TO ROAM ACROSS
THE ROCKET MARTIAN TERRAIN.
THE MISSION IS NEARLY COMPLETE
BUT ONE ELEMENT IS MISSING, AND
ITS NAME HAS BEEN REVEALED.
IT HAS BEEN NAMED TO DAVID --
NAMED TO THE ROSALIND FRANKLIN
ROVER.
>> ROSALIND FRANKLIN, A GREAT
BRITISH SCIENTIST WHO DID SO
MUCH TO UNLOCK THE SECRETS TO
HUMAN LIFE WITH THE DOUBLE
HELIX, IT IS ONLY FITTING THAT
THE MARS ROVER IS NAMED AFTER
ROSALIND BECAUSE IT WILL BE
SEARCHING FOR SIGNS OF PAST LIFE
ON MARS.
REBECCA: YOU GOT THE PUBLIC
INVOLVED IN THE NAMING PROCESS.
>> THE COMPETITION WAS OPEN UP
TO THE PUBLIC, 36,000 ENTRIES
HUGE RESPONSE.
IT SHOWS THERE IS SO MUCH PUBLIC
APPETITE FOR THESE EXPLORATION
MISSIONS.
REBECCA: IT REALLY IS A BIG
MISSION FOR THE EUROPEAN SPACE
AGENCY.
WHY IS IT SO VITAL?
>> IT IS A REALLY EXCITING
MISSION.
THIS ROVER IS GOING TO DRILL TWO
METERS UNDER THE SURFACE OF
MARS, AND THAT IS WHERE WE STAND
THE BEST CHANCE OF DISCOVERING
ORGANIC MOLECULES THAT COULD
HAVE RESIDED ON MARS.
IT GOES TO A SPECIAL LANDING
SITE, WHERE THERE WAS ONCE A
LIQUID OCEAN.
WE KNOW THAT 3.7 BILLION YEARS
AGO, EARTH AND MARS WERE
SIMILAR.
LIFE COULD HAVE EVOLVED ON MARS
AS WELL.
REBECCA: THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THIS IS OBVIOUSLY A ROBOTIC
MISSION HEADING TO MARS.
THE REAL THING HAS BEEN
ASSEMBLED AND SCIENTISTS ARE
WORKING AROUND THE CLOCK.
IT REALLY WILL BE A FITTING
HONOR FOR THE WOMAN WHO TRULY
WAS AN UNSUNG HERO OF SCIENCE TO
HAVE THIS LEGACY THAT WILL NOW
LIVE ON MARS.
JANE: REBECCA MORELLE REPORTING
THERE ON THE ONGOING QUEST.
YOU CAN FIND MORE ON ALL THE
DAY'S NEWS ON OUR WEBSITE.
TO SEE WHAT WE'RE WORKING ON AT
ANY TIME, CHECK OUT TWITTER.
I AM JANE O'BRIEN.
THANKS FOR WATCHING "BBC WORLD
NEWS AMERICA."
>> WITH THE BBC NEWS APP, OUR
VERTICAL VIDEOS ARE DESIGNED TO
WORK AROUND YOUR LIFESTYLE, SO
YOU CAN SWIPE YOUR WAY THROUGH
THE NEWS OF THE DAY AND STAY
UP-TO-DATE WITH THE LATEST
HEADLINES YOU CAN TRUST.
DOWNLOAD NOW FROM SELECTED APP
STORES.
>> FUNDING OF THIS PRESENTATION
IS MADE POSSIBLE BY
THE FREEMAN FOUNDATION,
AND KOVLER FOUNDATION, PURSUING
SOLUTIONS FOR AMERICA'S
NEGLECTED NEEDS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> POSSIBILITIES.
YOUR DAY IS FILLED WITH THEM.
>> TV, PLAY "DOWNTON ABBEY."
>> AND PBS HELPS EVERYONE
DISCOVER THEIRS.
ANYTIME, ANYWHERE.
PBS.
WE ARE WITH YOU FOR LIFE.
>> "BBC WORLD NEWS" WAS
PRESENTED BY KCET, LOS ANGELES.
>> Announcer: