These women love the scents in
this ground breaking art exhibit
It smells Amazing
Luxurious
But what are the smelling?
Wait, it's Suave?
Wow.
It's Bodywash.
No it's not.
I can't believe
this is Suave.
Can I take this home?
Suave Body Wash.
Fragrances as Beautiful
as Bath & Body Works.
Let's talk about
Haribo Goldbears.
■&9&9&■■■■■■■■4L■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■@
The red one is more
gooder to me
cos it tastes like berries.
They're really squishy.
And then I'm gonna fly
it in to my mouth.
♪ Kids and Grown
ups love it so ♪
♪ the happy world
of Haribo
- All right, we're back.
- All right.
So yesterday,
we did some research.
- We don't know what
to make of this.
- We're a little befuddled.
Okay, so here's
where we started.
So the first thing we found
when we searched his number...
Bingo.
- Look what we got.
Number for five years.
Comes back to a Matt [bleep].
- This never happens.
It's in Florida, which
is where he says he lives,
so this was kind of
a good surprise,
and he also has a Twitter.
Then there's some pictures
back from 2012
that look like they're of him.
This would have been the Matt
that you sort of
started talking to.
- Then we looked up his URL.
The first one was oa bunchh
a PlentyOfFish account
that's up; I don't know how
or when it was last active.
For a guy who lives in
Kissimmee, 21 years old, 6'2".
There's also this photo.
It could be him.
- I'm not sure if I should
even make a comment.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
I'm not sure what to say.
- What's--are you upset?
I can't tell...
- Do you mind
if I take a second?
- Sure.
Yeah.
Take as much time as you need.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
You all right?
- Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪