I was like,  "You kn?
"Instead of kind of,
like, avoiding him,
this dude needs help.
Let me do what I can,"
but lately, I haven't been
in contact, so...
- What about Natalie?
- [laughs]
Uh, you know,
I never contacted her.
You know, it's just--I just
been focusing on myself, man.
So, thank you for everything.
- All right.
- Thanks, Danny.
Good talking to you, man.
- Take care.
God bless, you guys.
- All right, we'll see you soon.
- Later, bro.
[line trilling]
- Hola!
- Hey!
- Hey, how you doing?
- Wow, look at this guy.
- Wow, look at--
you're all cleaned up.
- Yeah, nice haircut.
- Yeah.
- Oh, thank you, thank you,
thank you.
- You look good.
- I mean, what--
- You look like
you lost some weight too.
- Yeah.
- I been working out.
- What?
- No way!
- Yep, you guys helped me
a lot.
- Tell us everything.
- Well, I actually
got my own place now.
Been very exciting, you know?
Living here is great.
I'm working for
a new company now.
I really like it.
I'm still doing door-to-door.
- Sales?
- Sales.
I love sales.
Thank you, ma'am.
Have a great day.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- That's what I like to do.
That's me,
en going to church.
- Really?
How's that been going?
- When I go there,
you know, I feel more peaceful.
I feel comfort.
I feel like
that's where I belong.
- That's nice.
Have you made any friends
through the church?
- I have made
a couple of friends.
I'm kind of talking
to somebody right now.
- That was my next question.
Who--who are you
kind of talking to?
- I'm not gonna put his name
out there or nothing like that.
Someone you met
on the Internet?
- No, I did not meet
on the Internet.
It was actually
one of the customers that I met
knocking on the door.
- Hey, all right.
Maybe you didn't make a sale,
but you definitely got a tip.
- No, I did make a sale.
- Oh, you did make a sale?
Oh, great.
- Yeah.
- Have you been talking
to Danny at all?
- Danny was a great person,
but Danny's somebody
that I wanna leave in the past.
Right now I'm very happy.
I'm closer to my family now,
and it's just amazing
waking up every morning
and just knowing
that you don't have
to make no lies up for the day.
You don't have
to live a double life.
What a transformation.
- I'm happy.
A total transformation.
- Yeah, it's like night and day.
- Thank you.
- These are the best kind
of check-ins
that we can ask for.
- Thank you very much.
- Enjoy the rest of your Sunday.
Good luck with eve
going.
Okay, thank you, guys.
- All right, see you, Jose.
- All right, bye, Jose.
- See you!
Okay, thank you, guys.
- All right, see you, Jose.
- Oh, boy.
We got a situation.
Quan,
"but we've never FaceTimed."
- Do you not have
a lot of people
who you feel like
you can confide in?
- I live in LA.
This is the land
of the fake and the phony.
I'm about to be like,
on TV looking crazy right now.
Oh, my God.
- Oh.
[dramatic musical sting]
[upbeat music]
- Hello.
- Zeke!
- What's up, man?
- Hi.
Nice to meet you.
- Zeke Thomas,
son of Hall of Fame
basketball player
Isaiah Thomas,
has paved his own path
as a renowned DJ and producer.
When he's not spinning
at the club,
he's traveling the country
speaking out against
sexual assault.
A modern-day Renaissance man,
we are so thrilled
to have Zeke.
- Nice to meet you.
- Welcome to the show.
- Thank you.
- So,
Little bit more about yourself.
When did you get started
into music?
- So, my dad being
a basketball player,
we actually had a basketball
court in our house.
- Indoor.
- And...indoor.
Whenever he was practicing
and I would be with him,
I was always
more concerned with
what we were listening to.
So we'd be, like,
shooting hoops,
and all of the sudden
I'd be like,
"Okay, we gotta change
the song."
So from then on
it was just like
music was my dream.
Worked my way up from there.
- Nice.
And when you travel
and you speak
about sexual assault--
because that was an experience
that you went through.
- Yeah, so, unfortunately,
I met a person on an app
and we went on a date.
I was actually drugged
and then assaulted.
- That's terrible.
■■■■
■■■■■■It was an unfortunatesitu■
I was actually drugged
and then assaulted.
- That's terriblBut it just went
■■■■         to prove to me that
not everybody is who they
present themselves to be.
- Right.
- I didn't really
do my homework.
And I want people
to do their homework.
- Right.
- And I think, you know, that's
- Awesome. Why don't we, uh,ited
to come ontow.q■
dig in?
- I'm nervous, but I'm ready.
- You're gonna be great.
Whoa.
We got an email here
from Truth.
"Hey Nev and Zeke, I'm Truth.
I'm 23 years young..."
- That's making us feel old.
- Yeah, I know, right?
- [laughing]
- ♪ I'm 23 ♪
- "I'm a fashion design
student in Los Angeles,
and I'm in dire need
of your help."
- ♪ This ain't about you ♪
♪ This is about me ♪
- "Six months ago,
I met Ray'Quan
"in an Instagram group chat.
"Ray'Quan is 22, and I think
He lives in Trenton,
New Jersey."
- ♪ Is it all in my head,
what they said? ♪
- "When I joined the group,
I noticed Ray'Quan
Was subtly flirting with me."
- ♪ I'm feeling
misunderstood ♪
- "So I reached out to him
privately.
"After messaging for a bit,
we exchanged numbers
"and began to converse
on the phone
"through both text messaging
and talking.
"He's a great listener,
"and when I tell him
my problems,
"he gives me great advice.
Compared to all the fake
people I've met in LA..."
- There are no fake people
in the tri-state area.
- Yeah, exactly.
- "Ray'Quan was something new
and refreshing."
- ♪ I fall in and out
of love ♪
- "But"--there's the "but."
- All right.
- "As great as Ray'Quan
sounds..."
- ♪ I really don't know
what I'm doing ♪
- "We've never successfully
FaceTimed."
- That's a red flag.
- "And two months ago,
I told him
"I had purchased a ticket
to come and see him.
"But when the time came
for me to visit,
He changed his mind."
- ♪ I'm feeling
misunderstood ♪
- "And I realized he might
be hiding something.
"I haven't questioned him
as much as I should,
"because when I do
ask questions,
he'll block or ignore me."
- Block?
- "That may not be ideal
for other people
and their relationships,
but I like a little crazy."
- So you're crazy.
Okay. We got a crazy one.
- Oh, yeah.
"I can deal with his temper..."
;;>C■
"I'm■
77■■7/ "You're my last resort,
"I can deal with his temper..."
"and I hope to hear
from you soon.
Truth."
This episode's gonna be tricky.
Because the person
we're trying to help,
their naTruth.
So every time
we're talking about them,
and whether or not
they're getting lied to,
it's gonna be confus
an- It's going to be confusing.
they're gett- Right. to,
Is Truth getting the truth?
- Is Truth getting the truth?
Is Truth the liar?
- Can we trust Truth?
- I don't know.
- [laughing]
- Why don't we just get
a little bit more
from Truth here.
[FaceTime ringing]
Hey.
- Truth.
- Hey.
- What's up?
- I love your hair.
- Thank you, thank you,
thank you.
I just dyed it.
- Wow, is that--
- I just did mine too.
- Sorry, I should
introduce you.
So, Truth, this is Zeke.
- Pleasure to meet you
as well.
- He's helping me out
on this episode.
We just read your email.
So you're in Los Angeles?
- Yes.
- And you're at a school
for design, you said?
- Yeah, fashion design.
- Nice.
- So I have a question for you
off the bat.
You were in a group chat
with this individual.
- Right.
- Ray'Quan.
Who else was in
this group chat?
- A mutual friend
between ours, Kevon,
and then some other people.
- Kevon, is that a real--
a friend that you know
in person,
or just like a friend from...
- From Instagram.
I never met him.
- Right.
In the group chat,
he's been mean.
I don't like him.
Kevon, he got an attitude.
Like, he's this very--
a dark cloud, negative.
- So you didn't know anybody
in this group chat
personally.
- No.
- Tell us what you do know
about Ray'Quan.
- The first month
we was just, like,
getting to know each other.
And then I was like,
"Okay, I kinda like him."
'Cause he's, like,
a great listener.
Usually when we're talking
I, like, vent a lot
about what I'm going through
and, like, what's going on
in my life.
And he gives great advice
and, like, good feedback.
- But he always says no
to FaceTime?
- Yeah, he has, like,
a lot of excuses
about why his phone's
not working.
I don't wanna keep bugging
him about FaceTime
because he, like, gets mad
sometimes and he blocks me.
So I was like, okay,
better not make him mad.
Because I don't want to get
blocked for a week again.
- You got blocked for a week?
And then you still
talking to him?
- Yeah. I like crazy people.
I'm attracted to crazy.
- How do you know for sure
he's in New Jersey?
- Now you're making me think.
I don't know.
I hope he's there.
That's what he told me.
- Oh, now you got
his mind working.
Truth gotta find the truth.
- All right, well, look.
You're in Los Angeles.
We're in Los Angeles too.
Why don't we plan on meeting up
tomorrow morning
to see if we can
figure this out?
- We gotta do something,
'cause I'm over it.
- Maybe you could have
an outfit or something ready
for Zeke here.
You could try--
you could style him.
- Yeah, 'cause you need
some help.
- Oh!
- You know what?
Okay.
Okay, Truth.
- We'll see you
tomorrow, Truth.
- All right, bye.
- I'm not sure Truth
is telling the truth.
ñ■
- Really?
- Something's not computing.
- You think he's leaving
something out?
■@■Yes.
- All right, well,
I'll see you in the morning
and we'll find out.
Come ready for a makeover.
- ♪ Feeling like a boss ♪
♪ And staring at the stars ♪
- Here we are.
In the Valley.
- In the V>@>@
- ♪ Everybody ♪
♪ Wants to be famous ♪
- Let's do it.
- ♪ Staring at the stars ♪
- Hey.
- Hello!
- Hey, what's up?
- How's it going?
- This morning I actually
really was thinking about
what I was wearing,
because you were ripping me
yesterday.
- Okay. Okay.
- Oh, here we go.
- I made all of these.
- You made all these?
- Yeah. I'm about to be famous.
- All right, well,
we gotta have a show.
- We need music.
- Oh, he takes it off.
Whoa.
- ♪ Everybody wants
to be famous ♪
♪ Everybody wants ♪
- So here we are.
You gave us, like,
a little description
- Right.
of - Your friend invites youn.
into this group chat.
- Kevon.
- Well, we're not friends.
He's, like, fake.
- Fake, like, not the person--
- No, like a fake person.
Like...
- Right.
- Somebody that...
- He's not a good person--
- He's just...
- Got it.
- 'Cause, like, he's,
like, in the industry,
like, styling, but,
- All right. So.
Like, just kinda take us back
to that first day
when you first sort of
set your eyes on Ray'Quan.
- Okay, so, we were, like,
in this group chat
on Instagram.
And we were, like, sending
memes and fashion stuff.
After, like, a week
of doing that,
I was like, "Okay, w■;    D"
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■,
getting to know each other
or what do you like to do,
what I like to do.
Like, I was venting and telling
him about my life,
what I want to■■■■■■■■■■I am
and stuff t.
Majority of the time
we're on the phone,
I talk more than him.
That's why I say
he's a great listener.
- Do you generally not have
a lot of people around you
who you feel like
you can confide in?
- I live in LA.
This is the land
of the fake and the phony.
- Well, let's talk
about that for a second.
So, 'cause, here you are
in Los Angeles,
one of the hubs
of gay community.
- Mm-hmm.
- Can't you find someone
you'd be interested in here?
- Because I've kinda--
I've been dating somebody else.
- Okay. Okay.
- Okay.
- There we go.
- Spill the tea.
- It's a girl.
both: Oh.
- Is that, like, kind of
a serious thing, or...
- Yeah, we've been dating
for a year.
- Really?
Does she know about...
- No.
- Ray'Quan?
- You do like the drama.
- The drama likes me.
I don't like drama.
Drama likes me.
- Are you guys, like,
taking a break, or...
- No.
But Cierra just went back home
for, like, six months,
and then she's gonna come back.
I was like, well,
might as well try to...
see what's up with him 'cause
she's gonna be gone
for a while.
And I'm, like, bored--
I don't want to be bored.
- Does Ray'Quan know that
you have a girlfriend?
- No.
- Does Cierra think
you guys are exclusive
and monogamous?
- Yes.
- Does Cierra know
that you also date men?
- No.
But I love both of them.
We could all be a throuple.
I think we could be, like,
I want to be with
the both of them.
- Okay.
- Do you think she'd be down?
- You never know.
- Wow.
- Cierra makes you happy?
- Yeah, she's, like,
really good.
Like, to talk to too, and--
- So why--what's
stopping commitment?
- I'm only 23,
and I'm not trying to be,
like, married right now.
- Fair.
- Yeah.
But I do think Cierra deserves
the respect of being kinda
filled in on the situation.
While we want to help you,
we also don't wanna participate
in what Cierra would probably
think of as cheating.
It'd be nice, I think,
to kinda fill her in.
So think about how and when
you want to do that.
- Okay.
- Okay. Can we see a picture
of Ray'Quan?
- Okay.
- Show us your...
- Your profile.
- Your conversation with him.
- This is my.
That's me.
Y'all know that's me.
- Oh, you got 38,000 followers?
- Yeah, I'm lit.
You know.
- You got 38,000?
- Okay, okay.
- Look at me. I'm lit.
- You got more than me.
- Yeah.
- And can you show us--
- Cierra?
- Yeah. So this is her page.
She's very pretty.
- I made that.
- Oh.You made tha.
- You made that?
- Wow.
- You are very talented.
- And show us, uh, Ray'Quan.
Is that him, or?
- Yeah.
- Okay. He's
a good-looking guy.
- Can we look at the messages?
- Okay.
We was, like,
sending different memes,
and, like...
We were texting earlier
and I was like,
"Can you call me
on your break?"
He's been mean lately.
He gets so mad
when I call him babe or bae.
- That's interesting.
- I ow why he
be acting like that.
He's just a private person.
- I mean, is it possible--
have you ever considered
that maybe he's not
that into you?
- I think y'all are reaching.
- You guys ever say
"I love you"?
- I say it, but he'd be like,
"Yeah..."
- Like on the phone?
- Yeah.
He'd be like, "Uh-huh. Bye."
- Oh.
- He's never said it back.
- No, not that
I can recollect. No.
- We've got our work
cut ou
Send us an email
with everybody's profiles.
■■■
We'll see what we can find
and we'll meet back up
tomorrow.
I'm ready to dive in.
- I, like, really
[all laughing] dive inp
- It was nice meeting you.
- You too.
- Thank you so much.
[mysterious music]
- Oh, boy.
We got a situation.
- Potential situation-shrien
And a girlfriend.
çn■ne doesn't even know
much less is dating one.
It's a lot.
- It's a lot!
- It's a lot.
- We have a major situation.
- You were right.
You called it.
h was not telling
the whole truth.
Not much here,
except the usual.
What if we spice
things up a bit?
Alexa...
"Fire"
by The Ohio Players
♪Fire (uh) (uh)♪
What if we turn it up a notch?
♪Fire (It's all about) (Uh, uh)♪
What if we go off the map?
♪Fire (Woo, woo, woo)♪
♪Fire♪
The all-new RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
I can't believe it.
That there's a lobster
in our hot tub?
Lobster: Oh, you guys.
There's a jet!
Oh...I needed this.
No, I can't believe how
easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
r insurance with GEICO.
We could have been doing
this a long time ago.
So, you guys staying
at the hotel?
Yeah, we just got married.
Oh ho-ho! Congratulations!
Thank you.
Yeah, I'm afraid of
commitment...
and being boiled alive.
Oh, shoot.
Believe it.
GEICO could save you 15% or more
on car insurance.
That guy's the worst.
Brushing only reaches
25% of your mouth.
LISTERINE® cleans
virtually 100%.
Helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%.
Always go for 100.
■■
Bring Out the Bold™
■
There's a lot of stuff Michael
follows online.
Then he tried Tostitos
Scoops and Salsa...
and he started following
them in real life.
♪
Hey, Mike.
Sup.
Oh!
Tostitos.
Get together already.
Howdy Folks!
Try my $20 Fill Up,
you have ten seconds
to comply.
Shhhh.
You now have five seconds
to comply.
Four, Three, Two...
Try Any $20 FILL UP AT KFC.
L'OREAL PARIS INTRODUCES
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
LESS TEXTURE
MORE COLOR
LESS EXCESSÑ■Ñ■■■Ñ■Ñ■T
ALL DAY MATTE
BARE LIP SENSATION
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
BY L'OREAL PARIS
WE'RE WORTH IT
♪
T-Mobile is always happy to see
you.
When you join T-Mobile you get
two of unlimited
with two of the latest phones
included
for just one hundred bucks a
month.
(CLUCKING NOISES)
EVERYONE WANTS TO BE
THE CADBURY BUNNY
BECAUSE ONLY HE BRINGS
DELICIOUS CADBURY CREME EGGS.
WHILE OTHERS MAY KEEP TRYING,
NOBUNNY KNOWS EASTER
BETTER THAN CADBURY!®
That makes sense...
so if I bought it for
a business I started,
I'm able to deduct it?
Yes, that's definitely a
deductible expense.
That was really helpful.
Man, I love technology,
but it is infinitely
better with people.
xx  you nereal
human touch you know?
■Like I was saying, humans and
technology working together.
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■.
TurboTax Live now
with CPA's on Demand.
Don't let your longwear
weigh you down.
New Infallible Fresh Wear
Foundation by L'Oreal.
■■■ Get longwear coveragefrom o,
breathable formula.
Defies sweat and transfer.
Stays fresh. Feels light.
All day to night.
New Infallible Fresh Wear
by L'Oreal.
Hey neighbor!
See this sweet feature?
t call it a spoiler,
on't spoil a thing.
Oh look,
you don't need to sell me.
At CarMa■■÷÷X■■■■■
That's helpful.
This is just taped on for show.
They'll still buy it.
you.
■u■u■u  - All right.
[groans]
■÷started,
let's have a little treat.
- Can we "cheers"?
To Truth!
- Oh, yours,
yours is, like, giant
compared to mine.
- [laughing]
- Let's just recap.
- Mm-kay.
Truth, 23 years old,
let's call him bisexual.
He has Ray'Quan.
- Met him on Instagram
in a group chat.
- And they were
introduced by...
- A guy named Kevon.
- Kevon.
Truth is currently dating
a girl, Cierra,
for a year.
- He's dating two people.
So now we've gotta figure out,
who is Ray'Quan?
Is he the guy in the pictures
who lives in New Jersey
or someone else?
Quite a debacle.
- It is.
- It's a mess.
- Truth sent an email.
Mm-kay.
- Ray'Quan's phone number,
his Instagram.
Selfie.gawdd.
"I don't have a number
for Kevon"--
right, 'cause they've
never met in person--
"But here's his Instagram."
Okay, let's just search
Ray'Quan's phone number.
We'll do a quick search here...
See what we get.
No name.
- Trenton, New Jersey, however.
- Okay, New Jersey checks out.
All right, so here are
pictures of Ray'Quan.
And let's see
if any of these come up.
A
All right. First one.
both: No.
Second pic.
Okay, nothing.
Last picture.
- Oh--no.
- Nothing on the pictures.
So let's just look a little bit
at his Instagram.
This is Ray'Quan's Instagram.
Selfie.gawdd.
- Six pictures.
How many followers
does he have?
- 2,700.
I mean, this feels like
a fake account.
- Let's look at the comments.
- Yeah, let's go
to the first post.
All right. Here we go.
This guy, hymnsofly,
commented on Ray'Quan's
oldest picture.
- The oldest picture.
Is he commenting
on anything else?
- Yes, the most recent photo.
Hymnsofly, "3 more weeks
I can't wait."
Maybe they know each other
in real life.
- Who's hymnsofly?
- Yeah.
His name is Dedrick.
- Private account.
- But we could message
and just say, like,
"How do you know Ray'Quan?"
Let's try hymnsofly.
- Hymnsofly...
- All right.
[chime]
All right, so we sent
a message to Dedrick.
So let's just look
to see if Ray'Quan
is tagged on Instagram.
Is he tagged in anything?
Okay, so this guy tagged
Ray'Quan in a photo.
commented
"I miss you."
Who is this?
- That's Kevon.
That's the friend.
- You're right!
So wait a second.
- That's Kevon.
- So there it is.
- So Kevon...
is in a picture
and personally knows Ray'Quan.
- This is a big deal.
's huge.
- That is huge.
- Okay. We need
to message Kevon.
If he can confirm that he
does, in fact, know Ray'Quan,
that'd be huge.
So sending.
All right, great.
Okay, so now we've got
messages out
to Dedrick
and this other guy, Kevon,
who...
- Yes.
- Is the link.
- Who's the link.
- And in the photo
with Ray'Quan.
- We've not searched for Kevon
on Facebook.
000■■right,
let's do that.
■
Oh, yeah, there he is.
-employed...
- Let's just see
what's on his page.
Wait, what's this?
Kevon was in Trenton.
- Okay, Kevon was in Trenton.
"Coming home tomorrow."
- Wait a second.
Trenton.
Exactly the same as Ray'Quan.
Huh.
Oh. Whoa!
Holy [bleep].
Kevon's Facebook--
t the URL.
x■íWk■÷■
- Oh, boy.
- Kevon's Facebook URL
is selfie.gawdd.
■■■/■■■s=
It's almost the exact
same thing
as Ray'Quan's Instagram.
That right there
is almost enough
to sort of...close the case.
- Truth has never
hung out with Kevon.
- Right, so he hasn't really
heard his voice.
- And has never talked to him.
- Right.
- I bet you Ray'Quan
doesn't exist, right?
- Truth's been talking
to Kevon...
% %ght. He  % %on
■7■■
- Truth's been talking
The one thing that, like,evon...
Truth has said--
- Truth was adamant about.
- Is that, "Oh■tand Kev"
- Right. Kevon's, like,
he's a mess.
■■■■He's always, like,
in people's business.
And now there's a good chance
Kevon and Ray'Quan
are the same person.
[phone ringing]
Oh.
From Annapolis, Maryland.
- Hello?
- Yeah, hey, who's this?
- Dedrick. Are you hymnsofly?
- Hey, what's up?
We're talking to someone who's
been texting and talking
to your friend Ray'Quan.
You commented on
one of his photos.
- Yeah.
- Do you know him in real life?
- Can you tell us a little bit
about him?
[phone beeping]
- Oh.
Did he just hang up?
Should we call him back?
- Yeah.
- Your call has been forwarded
to an automatic...
- Shady.
No call back, goes straight
to voicemail, like...
Could this just be Kevon?
One of his many characters?
This could get really ugly.
- It's malicious.
- All right, so, look.
So here's what we know.
We know that Kevon
was the connection
between Ray'Quan and Truth.
- Kevon has
the same Facebook...
- URL.
- URL
as Ray'Quan's Instagram.
- So there's a good chance
the Ray'Quan Instagram page
is fake
and Ray'Quan
was created by Kevon.
But Ray'Quan is tagged
in a photo with Kevon in it,
so the guy in the picture
is just someone Kevon knows,
but that's not Ray'Quan.
his profile.
- This is not his profile.
You know, you have
a circle of people
who all connect together.
And maybe people are trying to
blow up Truth's life.
(Nationwide jingle)
You see Brad,
songs are really about
big life moments.
Baby shower here.
Big. Life. Moment.
What is in here? Ohh!
Oh, I hope it's
a life insurance policy.
What?
It's a sensible gift.
Protection for you
and your family,
Nationwide has all the tools
to help you find
the right coverage.
Tiny baby shoes.
So close.
(Peyton)
Makes no sense.
Should have been
a life insurance policy.
Plus it would have been
a great song.
Think about it,
the lyrics,
the beneficiaries...
Brad, where are you going?
L'OREAL PARIS INTRODUCES
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
LESS TEXTURE
MORE COLOR
LESS EXCESS
Ñ■ IMPACT  MORE COLOR
ALL DAY MATTE
BARE LIP SENSATION
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
BY L'OREAL PARIS
WE'RE WORTH IT
The iPhone XR is a marvel in
technology.
Yeah.
This edge to edge screen is
unbelievable.
Am I nuts or does everything
look better on an iPhone?
Both.
And with our Unlimited plan,
people can choose the best in
entertainment.
HBO, Cinemax, Showtime...
STARZ, VRV, Amazon Music, or
Pandora...
Now people can get what
they want.
Because everyone's different.
I feel like we shouldn't talk
for a couple of days.
AT&T has the only unlimited plan
that gives you your choice of
top-tier entertainment.
Get an iPhone XR on us when
you buy the latest iPhone.
MORE FOR YOUR THING. THAT'S OUR
THING.
Brushing only reaches
25% of your mouth.
LISTERINE® cleans
virtually 100%.
Helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%.
Always go for 100.
■■
Bring Out the Bold™
[SFX]
Scuffle
Scanning sound
All white-meat.
Hungry Boy.
Enjoy!
Try an all white meat $5 fill
up at KFC.
;;;;;■■
Ready for a lash lift?
L'Oréal's new Unlimited Lash
Lift Mascara.
1. Stretch it.
2. Tilt it.
3. Lift it.
Reach even smaller lashes.
Unlimited length.
Unlimited lift.
New Unlimited Mascara by L'Oréal
Paris.
♪♪
HEYYYYY!■,■,■,■,■,■,
It's the
that■fe rich.■
Ritz.
■
When I believe in something,
I'm all in.
So if I'm gonna be blonde,
it's got to be great.
Superior Preference
from L'Oreal.
Translucent, liquid gel formula.
Luminous, fade defying color
that lasts.
With incredible dimension.
Preference from L'Oreal Paris.
New Trident Tropical Beat Vibes
start with a light crystal
coating,
then change into a smooth gum.
With bursts of mango peach
flavor that pop.
And pop, pop, pop.
New Trident Vibes.
A Burst of Something New.
■■■2      [phone beeps]
- Whoa, I got
an Instagram message
from Kevon.
"Truth's not my friend.
"I can't believe he thought
this was so serious
"That he had to get "Catfish"
involved.
He's so messy."
Uh-oh.
"I can't believe he thought
This was so serious."
That suggests that he knew
Truth was having
some kind of a conve
relationship
ç■
uan.
■■   It's looking more and more
like this could be our guy.
■
"Can you meet me by
my apartment in a few hours?"
"Yes that works."
I don't know.
[line ringing]
- Yo, Zeke.
- I got some news, buddy.
Do you want to head
to the office?
- Hey, hey.
- Hey, what's up?
- You watching me watching you.
- Kevon wrote me back.
Oh, wow.
He said, "I can't believe he
thought this was so serious
that he had to get "Catfish"
involved."
- Oh, boy.
- If he's saying
"I can't belie■■■■
o serious," then
Kevon knows that something's
been going on.
Now. Is that because
he is Ray'Quan?
- And the selfie.gawdd,
selfie.gawdd still plays.
- Right.
that because he's
reí@@>Quan
like--
- Mm-hmm.
- It sounds like
he doesn't like Truth.
- Doesn't like Truth.
- They're like...
- Not interested.
- Competing fash■x■8■x■xbe
with him
- They're like...
this whole time.terested.
- Mm-hmm.
- And this is, like,
■8
the group chat
and some■8■8■8■8    playing a...
joke on...
like a thing that they do.
It could bp catfis■>■■■8■8■8eal.
- But he said, "I could meet
you in a couple of hours
by my place."
- That's...
- And he gave me the address.
- That's pretty big news.
■
- We have a h Kevon.
Let's go.
[mysterious music]
I feel like by contacting
and meeting up with Kevon
the clock ha
the countdown to destruction.
it's only a matter of ti .
start to
- Mm-hmm.
- All right.
- Let's do it.
- Kevon.
Let's hang back here.
Ñ7
"Just got here..."
- [singing]
♪ Waiting on Kevon ♪
♪ Waiting for Kevon ♪
[suspenseful music]
Well, he's taking
his sweet time.
- It's not feeling good.
[phone beeps]
- Oh--[groans]
Now he says,
"Sorry, I cannot do this."
- Kevon's backing out?
- Something's going on.
- Wonder if he would
talk on the phone.
- I mean, I'll take
a phone call.
[line ringing]
- Your call has been
forwarded
to an automatic
voice message system.
- Maybe meeting with us
means revealing
that it's him...
doesn't want to admit
that he's in love with Truth.
- I think it definitely
plays into less of
he's into Truth
and more of
he's messing with Truth.
Or a group of people
is messing with Truth.
- Right.
Well, this is... concerning.
Let's head over to see Truth
still has to tell Cierra Right.
Well,about all this.cerning.
- Real people,
real emotions.
Real stand-offs.
- Yeah.
If he didn't have
anything to hide,
he would have showed up.
♪
Cats will do anything
for the irresistible taste of
TEMPTATIONS™ treats.
What are you doing?
Oh hey, check this out.
TEMPTATIONS ™.
All
It Takes
Is A Shake™.
All
It Takes
L'OREAL PARIS INTRODUCES
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
LESS TEXTURE
MORE COLOR
LESS EXCESS■■ IMPACT
ALL DAY MATTE
BARE LIP SENSATION
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
BY L'OREAL PARIS
WE'RE WORTH IT
-We're doing karaoke later,
and you're gonna sing.
-I know, it's not much,
but it's home.
Right, kids?
-Kids?
-Papa, Papa!
-[ Laughs ]
-You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
-Oh, yeah.
-This one is tiny like a child.
-Yeah, she is.
Oh, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most --
a home and auto bundle
from Progressive.
-Oh, sweetie,
please, play for us.
-Oh, no, I couldn't.
-Please.
-Okay.
[ Singing in Spanish ]
know.
óó■■■///    -Please.
-Okay.
This is the fries' show!
McDonald's World
Famous Fries...
Featuring Bacon.
Or is the crispy bacon
giving the fries
I'm gonna let
bacon think that.
What's that?
Couldn't hear you over
the
McDonald's Classics with
Baco happen to our Classics? to
Or to bacon?
Try for yourself
and decide.
I've been vaping,
but it's safer than smoking.
You know 1 juul pod contains as
much nicotine as 20 cigarettes.
[20 cigarettes]
Huh...
Vaping is like safer than.
[horn sound]
Vaping is safer.
Safer.
[horn sound]
Safer than.
[longer horn sound]
[horn sound]
Skipped the shampoo?
Keep the style.
Our firs■z for
non-wash hai.s■z■z■z■z
So you can keep
the defined curls...
the gorgeous
volume...
...the
fresh look.
Work it between
washes.
New from TRESemmé.
Hey, how ya doing? Uh, Phil.
Are you guys good with brakes?
We're OK.
Just OK?
We got a saying here.
If the brakes don't stop it,
something will.
That's not a real saying.
It is around here. I wrote it.
JUST OK IS NOT OK.
Especially when it comes to your
network.
AT&T is America's best wireless
network,
according to America's biggest
test.
Now with 5G Evolution. The first
step to 5G.
MORE FOR YOUR THING. THAT'S OUR
THING.
Howdy Folks!
Try my $20 Fill Up,
you have ten seconds
to comply.
Shhhh.
You now have five seconds
to comply.
Four, Three, Two...
Try Any $20 FILL UP AT KFC.
Ready for a lash lift?
L'Oréal's new Unlimited Lash
Lift Mascara.
1. Stretch it.
2. Tilt it.
3. Lift it.
Reach even smaller lashes.
Unlimited length.
Unlimited lift.
New Unlimited Mascara by L'Oréal
Paris.
■v■v■va■ ■17ying]
- Hey, Truth.
We've got a little bit
of a situation here.
We have some things
to tell you.
So where do you want
to meet up?
- Can we come there and talk?
- All right, man,
we'll see you soon.
- Hello?
- I'm back here, hey.
- Wow.
- Good to see you.
- Whoa.
This is cool.
All right, well, come on,
we got--
we got a lot to talk about.
Why don't we just
show you what we found,
and then we can decide
what we wanna do.
- Right.
- So yesterday you sent us
this email.
- You had given us
Ray'Quan's number.
- Right.
So we did a search to see
if that number
is registered to someone.
- Okay.
- And no name
associated with this number.
But Trenton, which makes sense.
And then we just thought,
let's see if he's tagged
in any photos.
He's tagged in two pictures.
- Okay.
- And one of them...
- Is with Kevon.
- Okay.
- So we sent him a message.
And we searched just to see
if Kevon had a Facebook.
And we found that he does.
But, more interestx  he's o,
exactly the same as Ray'Quan.
And then, check this out,
we looked at his URL...
His Facebook page
is selfie.gawdd.x
c■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
■■■■■■ Instagram
is selfie.gawdd.x.
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
- Okay, what?
So what you saying--
this is Kevon.
So he's playing in my face?
Like, what's going on?
Is--is that--
It's--like, what is--what is
going on?
- Kevon is the one
that invited you to the chat.
And Ray'Quan's Instagram page
and Kevon's Facebook page
have almost identical URLs.
So Kevon could be
the guy you're talking to.
Then...
- Today,
Kevon finally answered.
- He messaged me back
on Instagram.
So let me show you
these messages from Kevon.
- "I can't believe he thought
this was so serious
that he had to get "Catfish"
involved."
Oh, Lord.
- And he suggested meeting up
this morning.
- So we showed up.
- And he, like, bailed on us
after we got t
We tried calling,
but no answer.
- Okay.
- So that's when we called you
and came over here.
Is there any chance Kevon
has a crush on you
and likes you?
- He ain't never told me that.
- Well, right, but if he had,
would you have been
nice about it?
- No, I wouldn't.
- Well, you might not
have gone out with him,
but you wouldn't have, like,
been mean to him, right?
- Yeah, I would.
- You would've.
But then there's alsoith ■
this profile.
This guy, hymnsofly,
AKA Dedrick,
who commented on Ray'Quan's
pictures--
does he look familiar at all?
- Um, he might have been
in that group chat too.
- We messaged him.
And he called us yesterday.
And we were just
starting to talk,
and then click, it, like,
got disconnected.
- Got disconnected?
- Yeah.
Sketchy.
- Multiple people
might be in on this.
- I don't even know these,
like, him and this other guy--
I'm really like--
like■■■■Ñ■Ñ■ÑLike...
I'm gonna look dumb.
Like, I already look dumb.
I don't know him.
We ain't friends.
Like, seem like
they obsessed with me.
It just, like, seem like
they clout chasing,
like they wanna be pophing
■■
off of my expense.
I gotta go outside.
I can't breathe.
- Oh, boy.
- ♪ Damn I look good
on camera ♪
♪ ♪
- You wanna go out there?
Let him vent.
Just, you know, talk to him.
- You want some water?
- Yeah, I need some Fiji water.
- We got a water?
- Fiji water.
■ I understand how you feel.
Take these deep breaths.
Water's coming.
- I'm abe like...
on TV looking crazy
right now.
Like,
I just need some water.
- I'll go get ater.
- But not, like, nasty water.
Fiji water.
- Zeke was trying
to calm him down.
Would one of you
go get some Fiji water?
'em.ñññ
♪ ♪
How we doing?
Why don't we go back in?
- Okay. I think I'm better.
- Okay, good.
I know this is a lot for you.
We- Yeah.k.■
- So I guess at this point...
we call Ray'Quan.
- Okay.
- See what he wants to do.
Let him know
we're doing the show.
Let him know we want
to meet up.
See if we can make that happen.
See what he says.
- Okay.
[phone ringing]
- Please leave
your message for...
- Just...
hold on, let me text him.
If it's green, that mean
they blocked you.
Oh, it is green!
- Blocked.
- Oh, [bleep].
- So you're blocked.
Officially.
- Let's text Ray'Quan
from my phone.
"Hey, Ray'Quan, this is Nev.
"I understand a lot's
going on right now,
"so we're hoping we could
all meet up
and figure this out."
Delivered.
We're bound to hear back
from someone
at some point.
And if we don't, we'll meet up
tomorrow morning,
and if we have to roll up
on Kevon somewhere or...
whatever it takes.
- But you definitely still
need to let Cierra know...
what's going on.
- If people are starting
to hear about this,
it could get to her.
So...sleep on it.
- Mm-kay.
- Okay.
- All right.
Hang in there.
- Okay.
I'ma try.
- All right.
We're almost worse off
than we were when we started.
- Now we got Kevon,
who seems to be going dark,
■4
Ray'Quan...Truth.
- Blocked Truth.
- I mean, this could be
a really malicious effort
by someone to ruin
Truth's life.
- It doesn't feel romantic.
[phone beeps]
[phone beeping]
- Okay.
Ray'Quan texted.
"Please don't keep hitting up
close friends
"and asking them questions
about me.
"I'm over all of this
and I want it to stop.
"I know you're in LA with Truth
so I'm gonna come to you.
"I'll let you know
where to meet me
once I figure it out."
Someone's showing up tomorrow,
but I have no idea
who it's gonna be.
When I had acne,
I made up a lot of excuses
not to go out.
I am ill.
You know, I'm trying to be
less popular these days.
It's just, like, not a good day
for me, work-wise.
I have jury duty.
Tonight.
And when I was tired
of the excuses,
I got rid of my acne
with Differin Gel.
It has the only
prescription-strength retinoid
you can get without
a prescription.
It clears acne and prevents
future breakouts.
So if you're not going out
because your door
is "glued shut",
do things Differin.
Announcer: 7:35 remaining...
Tatum, with the drive...
( ♪♪ )
...and slams it down!
Gatorade studies
the best athletes
to create the most advanced
range of sports fuel.
Gatorade. You fuel us.
We fuel you.
to create the most advanced
range of sports fuel.
Now, New York inspired shades.
Super Stay Matte Ink
■■■■■■om Maybelline .■
Urban edge.
Liquid matte
formula.
Up to 16
hour wear.
Super Stay Matte Ink.■■■
B■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■ @
(in-store music)
Need a change of scenery?
KAYAK searches hundreds of
travel sites
— even our competitors
— so you can be confident you're
getting the right flight
at the best price.
KAYAK. Search One and Done.ú■■k7
■k
Everybody all set?l
Oh, any recommendations?
The salmon roll's OK.
Just OK?
Is it fresh?
Sort of. The chef had it this
morning.
Unfortunately he went home
sick...
but he left instructions
with Kyle!
This fish is raw.
Do we need a minute?■/■/ñ/
Yes.
JUST OK IS NOT OK.
Especially when it comes to
your network.
AT&T is America's best wireless
network,
according to America■est
test.
Now with 5G Evolution. The first
step to 5G.
YOU THAT'ING.
Almost time for me to go.
Well, what if I...
drove me home?
[♪♪]
Whatt track of time?
What if we took a leap of faith?
Whoo-hoo!
What if you...
missed my flight next week?
[♪♪]
The All-New RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
The All-New RAV4.
[SFX]
Scuffle
Scanning sound
All white-meat.
Hungry Boy.
Enjoy!
Try an all white meat $5 fill
up at KFC.
Don't let your longwear
weigh you down.
New Infallible Fresh Wear
Foundation by L'Oreal.
f Get longwear coverage
from our most lightweight,
breathable formula.
Defies sweat and transfer.
Stays fresh. Feels light.
All day to night.
New Infallible Fresh Wear
by L'Oreal.
What about this guy?
This guy's...
been through a lot.
Dogs bring out the good in us.
Pedigree brings out the good
in them.
Feed the good.
GGooo■ [upbeat music]
- Oh.
- Hey, hey.
- Whoa, bling, bling.
That is a good look.
- I like this.
Can we come in?
- I guess.
[chuckling]
- Your beard.
- Oh, yeah, I dyed it.
- I just noticed that.
- This is what
I'm feeling today.
- All right, so last night
when I got home at 11:00
or something,
I had this text.
- "Please don't keep
hitting up close friends
"and asking them
questions about me.
"I'm over all of this
and I want it to stop.
"I know you're in LA with
Truth,
so I'm gonna come to you."
- So either Ray'Quan really is
coming from New Jersey
and he's on a flight right now,
or it's someone in LA already
like Kevon,
and they are just sort of
doing a good job
of making it look like...
- They're traveling here.
- They're traveling.
- Our heads are spinning
just like yours are.
- Did you text him today?
- No. But I should.
"Hey, Ray'Quan..."
- So...
when Ray'Quan,
if Ray'Quan, you know,
gives us this address,
it's probably smart now,
if you haven't already,
to probably reach out
to Cierra.
- Look, if that--
this is your call.
You're gonna have to deal
with her at some point.
And it's not gonna
get any easier
once we meet Ray'Quan,
no matter who he is.
- I'm overwhelmed with stress.
- It just seems like
the right thing to do
to look each other in the eye,
say what you need to say.
- Okay.
I guess I can
just freestyle it.
[FaceTime ringing]
- You look nice.
- [groaning]
- So I'm just gonna
tell you this
because, like, it's a lot
that's been going on.
So I'm, like, with Nev.
- Hey, Cierra.
- Have you ever seen
the show "Catfish"?
- Yeah, it's about people
who meet on the internet
■7don't always tell the truth
and don't know
who they're talking to.
- So I was talking to
somebody online, dating them.
- And it's a guy.
- I'm sorry, but it's just,
like,
a lot going on, it's like...
It's more of, like,
I've never seen him,
so it's like
an emotional connection,
and then it might not
even be him.
- No...
- Okay. We're off.
[phone clatters]
- All right, well, look.
She's...
should be upset.
You were gonna have
to tell her at some point.
- Takes--takes courage
to do that.
I know it's hard right now
but in the long run,
it's gonna make a lot of things
better for you
both in this situation
and just in life.
- Mm-kay.
[phone beeps]
- Oh.
Text just came in
from Ray'Quan.
"This is where I am.
You can come and meet me."
- All right,
he's like around the corner.
Can we go there?
- Well, that's--that's
the--yes.
- Can we pull up right now?
- All right, let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
What do you think
?appe
- The only scenario
that I'm gonna be happy with
ay'Quan being Ray'Quan
and his phone just is broke.
'Cause any other scenario,
it's gonna be an issue.
- Right.
- 'Cause this is somebody
really playing with me.
- Yeah.
- They're, like,
playing in my face,
and that's what
you're not about to do.
Got me out here looking crazy.
All right. Let's park.
■■
Everyone ready?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
- All right.
You guys chill here.
- Wait with me.
- I'll k [dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, my God.
■;■;■;
- Are we being
stood up again?
- I don't know.
■■";■]■m■=!=ú=■p■1
Hey neighbor!
See this sweet feature?
Don't call it a spoiler,  c■
Oh look,
you don't need t<<÷■÷■■LL■÷■■
That's helpful.
This is just taped on for show.
They'll still buy it.
Than
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
Howdy Folks!
Try my $20 Fill Up,
you have ten seconds
to comply.
Shhhh.
You now have five seconds
to comply.
Four, Three, Two...
Try Any $20 FILL UP AT KFC.
Now, full coverage that
doesn't quit.
Super Stay Foundation...
from Maybelline New York.
With full coverage pigments...
Stays on. Stays flawless.
Up to 24-hour wear.
Super Stay Foundation
Only from Maybelline New York.
♪♪
HEYYYYY!■,■,■,■,■,■,
It's the little things■ mae
Ritz.
I'm a dancer,
casting directors will send me
a video of choreography.
I need my phone to work
while I'm on the subway.
You'll see me streaming a video,
trying not to fall.
(laughs)
(VO)
There when it matters.
Get $300 off our best phones.
Only on Verizon.
When I believe in something,
I'm all in.
So if I'm going to be brunette,
it's got to be great.
Superior Preference
from L'Oreal.
Translucent, liquid gel formula.
Luminous, fade defying color
that lasts.
With incredible dimension.
eference from L'Oreal Paris.
New Trident Tropical Beat Vibes
start with a light crystal
coating,
then change into a smooth gum.
With bursts of mango peach
flavor that pop.
And pop, pop, pop.
New Trident Vibes.
A Burst of Something New.
♪♪
[Whistle]
Nelson, you smell great.
And no sweat, either.
Wow, you're the
new team captain.
Degree Advanced Protection.
Ultimate protection activated
every time you move.
Degree.
It won't let
you down.
What about this guy?
This guy's...
been through a lot.
Dogs bring out the good in us.
Pedigree brings out the good
in them.
Feed the good.
Have a seat, Dan.
Hey, where's the food? What
kind of meeting is this?
There's no food, we just said
that so you would show up.
What?! No food?
There's someone we
think you should talk to.
Hey, Dan! Your coworkers told
me you haven't done your taxes.
I just want to say, you can call
a TurboTax Live CPA for help.
We'll help you get your refund
and get back to your life.
You'd really do that for me?
Yeah, Dan.
It's literally my job.
Thanks, guys!
So, there's no
snacks...nothing?
I brought kale.
TurboTax Live now with CPA's
on Demand.
L'OREAL PARIS INTRODUCES
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
LESS TEXTURE
MORE COLOR
LESS EXCEMORE IMPACT
ALL DAY MATTE
BARE LIP SENSATION
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
BY L'OREAL PARIS
WE'RE WORTH IT
■u■s■u■s■s
cking]
- Are we being
stood up again?
Yb      '.
- I don't understand.
■■          ■. He  - Hi.
- It's him!
- Okay, it's Ray'Quan.
- I cannot...
- What's up? Nev.
- Ray'Quan.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
- I think you know
who this is.
[suspenseful music]
■■■■■■■■■/'
- Okay...
-
■híhp   's u   - Ray'Quan.
x■@@■■Do you not want to hug me?
Like, I'm confused.
- I'm cooo.
- Why are you confused?
went to the extremekea littled
and just did all this.
You got people, like,
calling people I know,
asking about me.
- 'Cause I'm, 'cause, like,
you don't never answer
- Okay?he FaceTime
- You blocked me.
Why am I blocked?
- You were doing a little bit
too much for me.
- What did I do?
What's the problem?
- Yeah, I feel like
we're missing something.
- What did you--
what'd you come here for?
Are we tal■s■C■y■■r?
What's going on?
- I never said we was together.
When did I say that to you?
- Are you kidding me?
- You're Ray'Quan.
- Yes.
at's
An?■?■?■een you talking
to him this whole time?
- Mm-hmm.
- And only you?
- Just me, yeah.
- No one else
is involved in this?
- No.
- Kevon...
has nothing to do with it?
- No.
- So who's all these
other people then?
- Well, that--no,
so we were wrong.
So then the real question■■ññ■ ?
then for me is, like,
we got the impression
from Truth that you guys
were interesteq■her
and that there was
some chemistry
and that you were hopeful
that you'd meet up
■■■■?■O■O■■
and seat happens,
so it's strange to me that
this would be an inconvenience
when, in fact, it feels like
something you guys
might have wanted
to have done.
- I mean, if it was something
I would have wanted done
I would have had it done.
I flirted with him,
but as far as a relationship,
we never talked about
no relationship.
- The last six months
for you has been...
- It's just been somebody
to talk to.
A friend.
- So you donS■at anything you sd
over the last six months
gave him the impression
that you were interested in him
in a meaningful way.
flirt you
elationship,
in ab■ole bunch
right now.
- Have you had feelings
for him?
- Yeah, he was a cool person
to talk to.
He still is a cool person
- If I'm a cool person,
■'t- Yeah, my phone, it works.
- So if your phone working,
why you never
couldn't answer FaceTime?
Answer that.
- Because I didn't want to.
- Why did you waste six months
of my life?
- You wasted your own
six months.
Nobody said that we were
in a relationship.
You did that.
- Are you dumb?
- No, are you dumb?
- No, are you?
- You're [bleep] stupid,
like, really?
Like, what was the point
of you coming
if you're gonna ac this?
- Because y're gonna
keep calling
and texting everybody asking,
so I came out here.
That's why.
- This [bleep] [murmurs].
I can't.
■■■çxxx■÷■÷wyu guys talk for a ■
This is Zeke, by the way.
Sorry.t.
x■x■x■x■x■■■■■■■■■
- Hi, how ■■■■
- You ñ■ñ■ñ■o■■
to meet.
I'll be right back.■=c-■c;- I's-
- Like, why--why'd y'all
bring me here
if y'all knew heonna
act like this?
- I didn't know it was
gonna be him.
- What the [bleep]
is wrong with him?
- I never said we was
in a relationship.
I never said that.
And then you going around
asking people,
having people call my phone.
"Oh, it's "Catfish,"
you going on "Catfish"?
Then you're trying to get
in contact with me.
That's embarrassing as hell.
- Well, I understand
your frustration.
- I'm frustrated 'caus,
■   an on-and-off-again
relationship.
That's why I never said
anything sexual to him.
I never said,
"Oh, you're my boyfriend,
Let's be boyfriends,"
'cause I'm not--
I wouldn't wanna bring
nobody in that.
- I don't know, I feel like
he's not telling us
the whole story.
Sounds to me like he might
have a boyfriend.
- I need to ask him
more questions.
- Sure.
- [sighs]
- Try to keep it cool
and collected.- [g lau■@■@■@
■@■@
- What's Kevon got to do
with this?
- What do you mean?
- He got something
to do with it.
Didn't he call you
or y'all was texting?
Got DM-ed or something.
- We--o's Dedrick?ed him.■
- A friend of mine,
a real close friend of mine.
- What?
- You're clout chasers.
■    'Cause they ain't more
a real clit than me.of mine.
I'm just about to say that.
■ ■ ■
They ain't more lit.
- Oh, they are, though.
Don't worry about nobody else.
- I am!
- Worry about yourself.
- I'm lit, like--
I want walk down--They want me.
- So if you so lit,
why you gotta go to "Catfish"
and stuff like that?
Go get you somebody else
since you're so [bleep] lit.
- Shut up.
- I'm very lit. I'm very lit.
- You're getting beside
yourself. Chill out.
- Who's gonna chill me?
I'ma stand right here.
You got a boyfriend?
- Yeahnd off boyfriend.
- So why you talking to me,
you got an on and off
boyfriend?
- Every time we chatted,
me and my boyfriend
wasn't together.
Like I said, on and off.
When I disconnected from you,
we were together.
respect you that much.
- You don't respect me
that much.
■■■ach other.id they were
on and oII
pXpX■8p■<÷O■R■R■SS■■■■
- I didn't deceive nobody.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
- You over here trying to,
like, be extra.
- I'm not trying to be extra.
- Yes, you are.
Because
why g this way?
- The only way for y'all
to clear the air
is to be 100%.
- And the thing about that is,
that's fun■2■2
I'm not upset about that.
Kudos to [bleep] you.
- No.
- I'm gonna go in your Airbnb
and sit down.
■Iust walking in
people's houses.
- You see, this is the type of
crazy [bleep].
Like nobody got the time
to deal with that.
- But you can understand
why he's upset, can't you?
- I can't.
- He said "I love you."
You could have, at that point,
been like,
"Yo, man,
I'm not feeling that."
- Wanna come--
■ú■nd--
we're just gonna defuse.
- How are we gonna defuse
the situation?
What's gonna defuse
- The only way to defuse
the situation is just...
be chill.
- Look, so somehow
he got the impression
ths
were much more serious
than you thought.
- He don't give a [bleep]
about nothing you saying, Nev.
Look how he's standing.
- All right, all right.
So let's--
- No one cares if he's
taking off his bookbag?
I'm not scared of you.
- See, what are you saying?
- Hey, hey.
- I'm not scared of you.
- Look at you.
-
- Look at you
with this mesh shirt on,
with these burgundy pants
and these black shoes.
- But you're uas [bleep] though.
■ ine, I love it.
- You're really ugly
as [bleep], like--
- That's fine.
- All right, let's go
for the moment
And maybe meet back up.
- Come on.
- And we can try
to sort of reset this.
- Okay.
- Let's go get some Fiji water.
- Nice meeting you.
- You too.
- Get this [bleep] mic
off of me.
Get this [bleep] off of me.
I'm out here looking crazy.
Take this [bleep] off of me.
[tense music]
Dumbass bitch.
■
Now, New York inspired shades.
Super Stay Matte Ink
from Maybelline .■■
Urban edge.■■
Liquid matte
formula.
Up to 16
hour wear.
Super Stay Matte Ink.■■■■
■■BB■@■@■@■@■@■@■■■@■■@■@■ ■@■@@
Don't let your longwear
weigh you down.
New Infallible Fresh Wear
Foundation by L'Oreal.
ffç Get longwear coverage
from our most lightweight,
breathable formula.
Defies sweat and transfer.
Stays fresh. Feels light.
All day to night.
New Infallible Fresh Wear
by L'Oreal.
When I believe in something,
I'm all in.
So if I'm gonna be blonde,
it's got to be great.
Superior Preference
from L'Oreal.
Translucent, liquid gel formula.
Luminous, fade defying color
that lasts.
With incredible dimension.
Preference from L'Oreal Paris.
I can't believe it.
That we just
hit the motherlode
of soft-serve ice cream?
I got cones,
anybody wants one!
Oh, yeah!
Get ya some!
No, I can't believe how
easy it was to save hundreds
of dollars on my car
insurance with GEICO.
Ed!
We struck sprinkles!
[cheers]
Believe it.
GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
or more on
car insurance.
From the Red Robin
kitchens.
Destined to be a
breakout burger.
The El Ranchero -
with candied bacon, onion straws
and a jalapeño ranch kick.
The first in our
limited-edition
Burger Masters Series.
[MNEMONIC]
RED ROBIN...YUMMM
The chicken always seems
to be a big favorite.
People love it.
You're not pulling it
out of a box,
you're making food!
Yeah.
I like being able to pride in my
food and pride in my work.
You get to walk right in and you
see me making your chicken.
This is gonna be in your bowl.
This is it!
This is it! This is it.
Reese's eggs are back
and we hid them
somewhere you'll never find...
Sike! We put them everywhere.
Grocery stores and
supermarkets, gas stations,
and chiropractor's offices,
bowling alleys,
and b7b&b&7sb&Y)■;■;7s■■■
Not Sorry, R
- All rio, look.
Now that you've had some time,
I texted Ray'Quan
to meet back up.
Let's just clear the air.
And if nothing else,
e things
on hopefully just
somewhat better terms.
Oh...
■■
That looks like
he's with Kevon.
- [laughs/groans]
Now y'all gonna be
playing in my face.
■■ didn't knt understand
was comwhy he's here.
- Hold on a second.
Hold on, h■■n.
- Why are you here though?
- He brought me here=p=p=t
And I'm here for support.
But also I came
because I heard, like,
the first conversation was,
like, super hostile,
so if it go down,
I'ma protect my friends.
- All right, let's--
let's just do one at a time.
I'm suredy
has something to say.
So first we now understand
that the relationship
that was taking place
between you guys
was different for you--
- Just, like,
a friendship to me.
- Fine.
Can you explain why
your Instagram page--
- Mm-hmm.
- Is selfie.gawdd.
- And your Facebook page.
- Mm-hmm.
- Is selfie.gawdd.
- Oh, that's something--
we're--we're, like,
elementary school
friends though.
- That was something
we did as a joke.
- You guys just came up...
- You're clowns.
- With that
when you were young.
- Speak when spoken to.
- What the [bleep].
- Let me just talk to them
for a second.
- Nobody's control
outh.
I'ma speak when I want to.
But, Kevon,
when we messaged with you
and you asked us
to meet you here
and then you didn't show up,
what was going on?
- Because he asked me not to.
- He called me.
- And I'm not a clout chaser.
I have my own clout.
Like I don't--I don't need
anybody else.
- I don't even know you.
- I wanna apologize
for how I came off earlier.
- What are you
apologizing for?
- He wants to apologize,
let's hear--
let's heut.
I wanna apologeke.
■■■■■
- Oh, my God.
- For how I came off earlier.
He was gonna get
pology, but--
- Oh, my God,
give him a Emmy
or a Golden Globe
or something.
He needs something.
- Get you a mother[bleep]
clipper, bitch,
'cause you look a [bleep] mess.
- You look a [bleep] mess
with this mesh shirt
and these burgundy pants!
It's not a look!
ú■   ■■ ■■■■■■■■■wanna do, boo?
- Truth didn't
come here to fig     ■■■-
- I can say what I wanna say.
- You're the antagonizer
right now.
You're the antagonizer
[indistinct shouting]
- Bitch, 'cause where I'm from
I will really beat you
the [bleep] up!
- Everybody. Everybody.
■E■■
- We got off
- on the wrong foot.dy.
- You're a [bleep] mess, bitch.
- No.
What you're not gonna do
is switch up words
in front of these,
what they said--
- You switched up words and
said we was in a relationship
when we wasn't.
- I never--did I say?
I said we were dating.
- We wasn't [bleep] dating
neither, dumbass.
- Clearly.
- Well, at the--at the--
- Could you just tell him
to be quiet while we talk?