- Your record hasn't been
that good, you know?
- I know.
- But you changed.
- The warm-up,
you have this guy here.
- Hey, you trying to take
my brother's job?
- Nah, nah.
Why don't you get
a haircut though?
(laughter)
- I don't have the means.
I only have 75¢ on me.
(announcer)
This is the courtroom
of Judge Frank Caprio,
where people and cases
are met with compassion.
A different kind of judge.
A courtroom
like no other.
This is "Caught in Providence."
- Bertrand Brousseau.
- Morning, Your Honor.
- Morning, sir.
Mr. Brousseau,
you have a, uh,
expired meter ticket
on Angel Street.
- I paid that three times.
- (laughing)
- Three times, and number--
Let me just give you
a little quick rundown.
- All right.
- My daughter works
on top of the bookstore
on Thayer Street.
- Yeah, okay.
- All right, third floor.
Her office is up there.
It was the day before
her birthday.
I went to drop
something off to her.
I-- She was busy.
I know that.
So I just dropped it off.
Took me 30 seconds.
30 seconds to get down
the stairs, up the stairs.
But anyways, um--
- You sure it wasn't
15 seconds?
- I-- It was closer than that.
I'm handicapped.
But, uh, anyways,
the, uh...
the meter had expired.
And I had put eight quarters
in the stupid thing
and it still
didn't go anywhere.
I put a sign on it...
"broken meter."
The lady tagged me anyways.
I went and found her.
I was probably in that office
15 minutes.
I said, you know, what is--
so, anyways.
But they were chasing me
and I kept paying 25, 25, 25.
It never got caught up.
I gave 'em 50 already.
- (chuckling)
- I think--
No, I think I gave 'em 75.
- Thought you gave 50.
- No, some-- well, somebody.
- No, don't fight
with a judge.
- All right, whatever you say.
Anyways, Your Honor--
- All right, well, let me tell--
(laughing)
Let me tell you what happened.
You got the ticket, right?
- Yeah.
- And you paid it.
- But when you paid it,
14 days had expired.
Listen to me.
14 days.
They give you 14 days
to pay the ticket.
- Okay.
- If you don't pay it
in 14 days, it doubles.
So what happened was
the ticket doubled
'cause you didn't pay it
in 14 days,
so you paid $25.
- Right.
- Right?
Then they sent you
a notice saying,
"You owe us another 25
'cause you paid that one late."
Then you didn't pay
that one for 14--
Then you waited 14 days
and you paid that one.
So they took that 25
and they sent you another notice
saying, "You paid
the second 25,
but you didn't do it
within 14 days."
- It's worse than
Bank of America,
you know what I mean?
- You're gonna pay 25
for the rest of your life
every two weeks.
- Right, exactly.
- All right, I'm gonna dis--
I'm gonna dismiss the balance.
- All right.
- Not only that,
I'm gonna give you a credit.
I'm gonna give you a credit
for the extra 25 that you paid.
- All right.
- Because you have
a red light violation.
- There you go.
- This is on Smith and River.
- Right.
- Do you wanna tell me
anything about that?
- Yeah, I'm gonna tell you
about that.
(laughter)
I was on my way--
- It's your daughter again.
I can tell.
- No, listen.
I was on my way to, uh,
say a prayer for you
and for everybody,
to Saint Jude Novena
up on...
on, uh, Chatham Street.
- You prayed for me?
- Yeah, of course.
And, uh... anyways.
The, uh-- I had bad news
from my doctor.
- If he's praying for me,
he's gotta go back,
do a little more.
- Listen, I had bad,
bad news from my doctor.
I was stopped at the red light,
first of all,
and I'm looking at it.
I wasn't texting.
I was just looking
to see what the--
what I had to pick up
and stuff.
And then I see
the light's green,
so-so I put it down,
then all the sudden
it turned red, boom.
52 years I wait my life
to see you.
- (chuckling)
- 52 years.
- You never had a--
- And I'm-- And I'm French.
- You never had
a moving violation?
- Never, never.
Except for that stupid
parking ticket over there.
I thought they were
gonna hang me for that.
- We're gonna take a look at it,
Mr. Brousseau, okay?
We're gonna take--
- Oh, no, I definitely--
I definitely went through it.
- Well, let me take
a look at it.
- Okay, if you want.
(Judge Caprio)
The light is yellow.
It's red.
Boy, you were speeding.
- No, I wasn't.
- Wow.
How fast was he going?
- (man) 34.
- 34?
You were doing
34 miles an hour.
Look at that.
- Maybe I did go through it.
(laughter)
I don't know why
I'm arguing with you.
Anyways.
- Wait a minute.
You just said to me
you were looking down.
- What I thought, yeah.
- You went right through
the light.
- Saint-- Saint Jude
wasn't driving, right?
- No, Saint Christopher,
he jumped out of the car
a long time ago.
- (Quinn) He jumped out?
He saw you were driving,
he jumped out.
(laughter)
- Inspector Quinn,
we have the--
we have the Saint Jude
defense today.
- (Bertrand) Anyway.
- You keep looking.
- I don't know.
Now I can't even see my car.
- Anything else
you wanna tell me?
- Nah, just tell me how much.
(laughter)
- All my friends are Italian.
They all grab my money.
You know what I mean?
- Ohh...
- (chuckling)
- Your Honor,
you're doing a good job.
And these-- the warm-up,
you have this guy here,
I don't know how come
he gets paid but to warm--
warm us up.
- (Quinn) Wow.
(Bertrand)
He's the warm-up.
- Now you're-- Now you're,
uh, buttering me up.
- Yeah, there you go.
I want his job.
Look at all the--
- (Judge Caprio) Oh, yeah, now.
- Look at the electricity
we're paying for.
(laughter)
- Now you're--
It's my brother.
- Ahh, that's why.
- You're trying to take
my brother's job?
- Nah, nah.
Why don't you get
a haircut though?
(Quinn)
Ooh.
(laughter)
- You guys are tough
on all these other people.
Be tough on me.
Arrest me.
- The parking ticket has been--
has been paid.
I'm gonna dismiss that.
- Okay.
- All right.
The red light violation.
It's your first one
in 52 years.
- Yeah.
- You paid $25 extra
for the, uh...
for the parking ticket.
So here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna charge you $35
court costs on the red light,
give you a $25 credit
that you paid
for the parking ticket.
So it's gonna cost you $10.
- For the whole thing?
(laughter)
And hey, give me the 10.
- (Quinn) Your Honor--
- Give me the 10
out of your pocket.
You said it'd be less
than that.
(laughter)
- Good luck.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- (laughing)
- Even though Mr. Brousseau
is French
and Joe is Italian,
they have one thing in common.
They love to bust ba--
excuse me-- bust chops.
- Hey, there you go.
I want his job.
- Now you're-- It's my brother.
- Ahh, that's why.
- You trying to take
my brother's job?
- Nah, nah.
Why don't you get
a haircut though?
(Quinn)
Ooh!
- When's the last time
you had a brain scan?
Kid looks like a movie star--
one that gets killed
in the first act.
- They are definitely brothers
from another mother.
Mr. Brousseau, I have known Joe
for over 20 years,
and trust me, it will take more
than a prayer to Saint Jude
to get the 10 bucks from him.
It will take a miracle.
See, I can bust ba--
excuse me--
chops too.
- I was fired from my job.
- You're in jeopardy now
of having the second car
forfeited to a tow company.
- They asked me
if they could take the car.
I told them no,
so I believe
they did it
without my permission.
With Advil Liqui-Gels,
you'll ask...
What stiff joints?
What bad back?
Advil is... Relief that's
fast. Strength that lasts.
You'll ask...
What pain?
With Advil Liqui-Gels.
Think only specialty stores have
what's new?
Olay has this season's hottest
debut.
Like new Clay Stick Masks.
All Mask, No Mess.
Olay Hydrating Facial Mist.
For hydration on the go.
And our breakthrough Brightening
Eye Cream.
Boosted with Vitamin C.
Get your new beauty fix.
Only by Olay.
- Lisa Pearson.
Lisa, you're charged
with going through a red light
on Service Road 8
and Broadway...
on July 15th.
Let's take a look at this.
Light is yellow.
It's red.
And you almost made it.
(man)
Red, Your Honor, now.
Here's her vehicle.
(Judge Caprio)
See where your vehicle is?
And the light just turned red.
- First of all,
I'd like to let you know
that I'm on disability.
Second of all,
I had my niece
and my nephew over,
and I believe they took my car
because I haven't had
any violations on my license
in at least five
to seven years.
So they asked me
if they could take the car.
I told them no,
so I believe they did it
without my permission.
And I believe
that he's the one
'cause I don't recall
going through no red light.
- This was at, uh, like,
5:00 in the evening.
Would that be you?
- Yeah, I-- no.
I don't believe it was me.
I believe the kids took the car.
I call them kids
'cause they're younger than me.
- Yeah.
(laughing)
- But, uh...
But, uh...
- You also have a ticket
for parking
in a loading zone
on Union Street.
I'm gonna dismiss
the loading zone ticket.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- But when your name came up,
they picked put his old ticket.
I'm gonna dismiss it.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- All right, now we have
to get back to the big--
big guns here.
This red light violation, okay?
I believe you, all right?
But here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna charge you $35
court costs,
and get it from them.
You hear me?
- Yes.
- 'Cause you are responsible
if someone who drives your car--
- Your Honor,
I can't afford it really
because I'm on disability.
And I only have,
uh, 75¢ on me
until my check comes the 1st.
I don't have any money.
And then I--
I bought my car,
and, uh, I--
- Lisa, Lisa, Lisa, Lisa.
I--
I'm dismissing it.
- Oh, God bless you.
Thank you, Your Honor.
- And good luck.
- I really, really appreciate
letting me be able
to not have to pay the fine
because I...
I don't have the means.
- All right, it's okay.
- I'm struggling.
And I'm trying to get
my condition together
with my disability, so...
- (Judge Caprio) Good luck.
- ...I'm trying my best.
(Judge Caprio)
Good luck to you.
- Thank you so much again.
- Bye-bye.
- Have a great day.
♪♪
- Patricia Lovely.
- Morning.
- Morning, Patricia.
You have two
red light violations
and three parking tickets.
- I thought
I was coming in
because I hadn't gotten a ticket
in so long
and I was going to talk to you
about the good driver thing,
and then--
- Yeah.
- I-- then--
- You got two red lights.
- I know.
- I'm gonna dismiss one.
- Okay, thank you so much.
- All right,
now what do you want
to tell me about
the parking tickets?
- Just that, you know, I-I--
It was right when they started
doing that thing where they--
you had a parking spot
and you had pay
down the street somewhere,
and I had no idea
how to do that.
- Oh, the multi-spacace meter.
- Yeah.
But I did do it, and I know that
that was this--
it was back then
when they started doing that
and I didn't know anything
about all that.
- Well, they got 'em
at three different locations.
It's not one location.
- I know, I know.
No, I know.
I'm bad-- it's my bad.
I'm just really happy to--
I wanna clear my slate.
- Are you ready to confess?
- I am.
I feel like this is confession.
- Inspector Quinn,
we have a confession.
- (laughing)
Your Honor, it's been a while
since I've been to confession,
so, uh...
- (Judge Caprio) Oh.
(Quinn)
...I can't fault the motorist.
- Well, while you're confessing,
we have a number
of unsolved crimes upstairs.
Do you wanna confess
to any of those?
We could clear them all out.
- Okay.
- What do you think,
Inspector Quinn?
- That-- I will accept
that confession,
Your Honor, all day long,
to clear the desk.
- All right, I'm gonna fine you
$85 for one of the red lights
and $30 for one
of the parking tickets.
- I appreciate that.
- So it's gonna cost you $115.
- Okay, thank you
very, very much, sir.
- Good luck to you.
- Okay.
- I know you can't be
his girlfriend
because basketball
is his girlfriend.
If I was standing next to you,
I wouldn't wear that T-shirt.
- Thank you.
- Donna Morales.
Good morning, Donna.
- Good morning.
- Donna, your car
was, uh... towed.
It was booted first.
It wasn't paid.
As a result, it got towed.
- Correct.
- The car got towed...
last month?
- Yes.
- Why did it take you a month
to come in here on this?
- Well, Your Honor,
I just, uh--
I was fired from my job.
I didn't have a job.
Um--
- No.
Well, let me go through this.
Your car was booted...
two months ago?
- No, that's, um, the Nissan.
I have my Infinity
that was just booted last week.
- Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
There are two vehicles here?
- Yes, two vehicles, but--
- Let me go through this slowly.
(chuckles)
The first vehicle is a Nissan.
I'm just-- I just know
what I have before me.
- Correct.
- It appears that that car
was blooted-- booted
a couple of months ago.
- Correct.
- And then towed.
- It's still at the tow company?
- Correct.
- Are you here
for that vehicle?
- No, I'm not.
Unfortunately, I--
The reason why it got towed
and I didn't come in--
I was not able to register.
I was in the process
of registering.
I bought it from a dealer
off of the Internet.
And something was wrong
with the title that--
so it looked like
three people were on there.
I was dealing with Miss Mancini
from the DMV.
She said, unfortunately,
we couldn't get it registered.
- Oh, you bought a car.
To use--
To use the street language,
the car was a gaffe, right?
- Basically, yes.
And--
- So, all right.
They had trouble with the title.
You bought it online.
You couldn't get it cleared.
All right,
I understand all that.
So you forfeited that car.
- Right.
- The tow guys got it, right?
- Right, so that's why I didn't.
- So you said, "Keep it.
I don't care about it."
- 'Cause you can't-- the DMV
said I can't register it.
- And... on the Infinity,
you had 11 tickets.
None of which were paid.
Most of them were
overnight parking
outside your house.
- Yes, Your Honor.
My landlord, uh--
I tried to file for the, um--
to see if I can get
the overnight parking ticket,
but because we--
there's six apartments
in my house,
the landlord had to go down
and do something, they said.
He finally just did it now.
And I lost my job.
That's why I didn't come in.
I'm just back to work,
so now I can take care
of the parking tickets
and everything.
I'm not here to give you
an excuse.
I'm fully responsible for it
and willing to pay.
- All right, Donna,
you're in jeopardy now
of having the second car towed
and forfeited to a tow company.
- Correct.
- So what do you wanna tell me
about these?
Did you come
prepared today to--
prepared to pay-- to pay
for the boot to be released?
- I have right now $300,
Your Honor, that I can give,
and then I could come back
every week
and make a payment
towards them tickets--
- Your record hasn't been
that good.
You know that?
- I know, I know.
- But you changed.
- I-I have a good job.
I lost my job.
I got a-- I'm back to work.
I am not losing--
I'm not gonna lose my job.
I have no other choice.
But...
(laughing)
But I will be making
the payments, Your Honor.
- In your defense...
In your defense...
'cause I really wanna be fair
with you, okay?
Almost all of these tickets
are parking in front
of your house overnight.
And I have some sympathy for you
because of that.
'Cause we have an ordinance
in Providence
that you cannot park overnight
on the streets in Providence.
And I know that many--
many landlords
don't have sufficient number
of parking spaces
for their tenants
and the tenants have no choice
but to park on the street.
All right, the original tickets
are $835.
The original tickets.
All right, I'm gonna dismiss
a number of the tickets
on Monticello Street.
It's gonna cost you
a $100 boot fee,
$300 for the tickets,
and I'm gonna release the boot
as soon as you pay the 300,
which will be today, okay?
- Okay.
- You have a $100 balance.
You're gonna have
a $100 balance.
- Okay.
- Try to pay that
as quick as possible
so that you can buy
a parking pass
so you can park the car in front
of your house for a year.
Okay, so as soon as you pay
the other 100,
you'll be eligible
to buy a parking pass.
- Okay, I can pay that
next Friday, Your Honor.
Thank you so much.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- I'm trying to help you
to help yourself,
so, please, help yourself.
- I definitely will.
I definitely will be here Friday
to pay that $100.
- Okay, good luck to you.
- Thank you so much.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- Rayelle Fernandez.
This is a parking ticket
on Benevolent Street.
- Yes, I never received it.
I just received the paper
in the mail,
so we came in today
to take care of it.
- All right.
So you're looking to waive
the penalties.
- Yes, sir.
- Yes.
- All right.
Who was driving the car?
- He was.
- (Judge Caprio) You?
- Yes, sir.
I was at work.
I work for a moving company.
- Now who's this?
- This is Rayelle.
- I'm the owner of the car.
- Are you friendly?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
(man)
I work for a moving company.
- I know you can't be
his girlfriend
because basketball
is his girlfriend.
(laughter)
- No.
- I mean, I'm not sure--
I don't want to get involved
here in any personal matters,
all right?
- No, I coach basketball, sir.
- Well...
- I coach.
- You know, just in case
she was disillusioned,
thinking that she had
a chance here, right?
His girlfriend
is basketball, so--
And he's proud of it.
See, so, I don't know.
If I was standing next to you,
I wouldn't wear that T-shirt.
- Thank you.
(laughter)
- Well, I think you should
discuss this after you leave.
If you need a mediator,
I'll mediate it, okay?
- (Rayelle) Okay.
- All right.
But I'm gonna waive
the penalties.
- Thank you.
- So she did a good job
talking for you.
I'd change that shirt.
(chuckling)
All right, it's $20.
- Thank you.
- Thanks a lot, Your Honor.
- Have a good day.
♪♪
You want a fresh-smelling home,
but some air fresheners use
heavy, overwhelming scents.
Introducing Febreze ONE;
a new range
of innovative air fresheners
with no heavy perfumes
that you can feel good about
using in your home
to deliver a light,
natural-smelling freshness.
Febreze ONE
neutralizes stale, stuffy odors
and releases a
subtle hint of fragrance
like Bamboo
or Lemongrass Ginger.
To eliminate odors
with no heavy perfumes,
try new Febreze ONE.
Brand Power.
Helping you buy better.
UGH... WHAT THE WHAT?
OKAY WIPE, PRETTY-PLEASE
DO YOUR THING.
NICE! NAILED IT!
HUGGIES® NATURAL CARE® WIPES,
GENTLE LIKE A HUG.
HUGG ON.
- I'll take the 50.
(laughing)
I'll take the $50.
- You plead the 50?
Used to be the 5th.
She pleads the 50.
(laughter)
- Um, yeah, that'd be--
I'll be fine with that.
You've explained I was,
you know--
- You wanna negotiate $49.50?
- (laughing) No, no, no.
- You wanna pay the full 50?
- Yes, I'll go for it.
- Okay.
(Judge Caprio)
Are you kidding?
♪ ♪ ♪
IF YOU HAVE RECURRING
CONSTIPATION AND BELLY PAIN,
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR AND
SAY YESSS! TO LINZESS.
YESSS!
LINZESS TREATS ADULTS WITH IBS
WITH CONSTIPATION
OR CHRONIC CONSTIPATION.
LINZESS CAN HELP RELIEVE
YOUR BELLY PAIN,
AND LETS YOU HAVE MORE FREQUENT
AND COMPLETE BOWEL MOVEMENTS.
SEE IF YOU'RE ELIGIBLE
TO GET 90 DAYS
FOR AS LITTLE AS 30 DOLLARS.
DO NOT GIVE LINZESS TO
CHILDREN LESS THAN 6,
AND IT SHOULD NOT BE GIVEN TO
CHILDREN 6 TO LESS THAN 18,
IT MAY HARM THEM.
DO NOT TAKE LINZESS IF YOU
HAVE A BOWEL BLOCKAGE.
GET IMMEDIATE HELP
IF YOU DEVELOP UNUSUAL
OR SEVERE STOMACH PAIN,
ESPECIALLY WITH BLOODY
OR BLACK STOOLS.
THE MOST COMMON SIDE EFFECT
IS DIARRHEA, SOMETIMES SEVERE.
IF IT'S SEVERE,
STOP TAKING LINZESS
AND CALL YOUR
DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
GAS, STOMACH-AREA
PAIN, AND SWELLING.
SO SAY YESSS!
TO HELP FOR RECURRING
CONSTIPATION.
YESSS! TO HELP
FOR BELLY PAIN.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
AND SAY YESSS! LINZESS.
- I was set up.
The guy who was crossing
was an undercover cop.
- Undercover cops,
they-- they count as
human beings, too.
- I witnessed something
that I thought was
both racist
and classist.
- I took one of the plates
from my old car
and put it
on the new car.
- You put it on two cars?
- Yeah.
- You convicted yourself now.
(announcer)
This is the courtroom