the technical defense.
"I was at my apartment,
I don't live there."
(woman)
- No.
- You could easily have said,
"I co-hosted the party,
and I told the police that
and that's why I'm here."
So, baby, you had to bring your
mother to court today, huh?
- I did.
- Are you still
spoon-feeding him or not?
Did you know that you could not
park there with a placard?
- I only parked
there 30 seconds.
- You were there 30 seconds?
- 30-45 seconds, ah...
- You keep talking,
they're gonna
take your
handicap placard away.
(announcer)
- This is the courtroom
of Judge Frank Caprio,
where people and cases
are met with compassion.
A different kind of judge.
A courtroom
like no other.
This is "Caught in Providence."
(Judge Caprio)
- Nicholas Damon.
- Good morning, Your Honor.
(Judge Caprio)
- Okay, Mr. Damon,
you're charged with
going through a red light
on Roger Williams Avenue
and Elmwood Avenue
at 10:18 in the morning.
Is this your
lawyer with you?
- This is my mother.
- I'm his mom.
- When are you gonna stop
taking care of these kids?
- I don't know.
- How long does it take
before you cut the cord?
- Never.
(Judge Caprio)
- That's a good answer.
- Now...
this is a classic case,
Inspector Quinn,
of a mother coming
to court for her little boy.
- Yup, it's her baby.
She's here for
her baby.
(Judge Caprio)
- She's here for her baby.
"I have to go to court
for my baby."
Do you have any
younger than him?
- No, no.
- No, only child.
(Judge Caprio)
- So he's your baby.
- He's my baby, yeah,
he's my only one.
- So, baby, you had to bring
your mother to court today, huh?
- I did, I did.
(Judge Caprio chuckling)
Hopefully it helps.
- Are you still spoon-feeding
him or not?
- No.
(Judge Caprio)
- No?
Well, he's...
he's charged with
going through a red light.
We're gonna look at it.
- Good.
- What is your name?
- Kerri.
- Damon.
Well, come up here.
Come up here,
come up here.
- You know, it's not
gonna end well for you,
so get rid of that smile.
- Get over here.
- Okay.
- We're gonna--
you've gotta give me a hand
on deciding this case, okay?
- Okay, all right.
- You've gotta be honest.
- I will be honest, yeah.
- All right.
- No special leniency.
- All right, so, okay, so--
- He hasn't had any...
- All right,
so I'm gonna get over here,
you're gonna get
over here,
and we're gonna look
at the video right here.
Okay, Lisa, let's go.
The light is red.
And...
- Uh... I thought it was
a right on red.
(Judge Caprio)
- Hold on for a minute.
The light is red.
He's coming down.
And he made
a right-hand turn.
Okay, now, what do you wanna
tell me about that?
- Well, he did
have his brakes on.
(attendees laughing)
And it was a slow,
it was a slow...
- You... you can take
a right turn on red over there.
It does have a sign
that says--
- I'm talking to your mother.
- All right, all right,
sorry.
- Be careful.
- I guess it was
a rolling stop.
- It was a rolling stop.
You don't
think he stopped.
(Kerri)
- Um...
No, he didn't
stop completely, no.
- You agree with that,
Inspector Quinn?
- She took the words
right out of my mouth, Judge.
(Judge Caprio)
- Yeah?
So what do you
think we should do with him?
- Um...
I don't know, I've done
a lot to him already
and screamed
at him about it,
and I-- I don't--
- Did you
beat him up?
- I didn't beat
him up.
No, I couldn't...
- Wanna use this?
- I could use this.
(attendees laughing)
- All right.
Like every mother,
like every mother, right,
she sees the good
in her son, right?
You're still her
little baby.
You can make
a right-hand turn on red.
At this location
you had to stop.
Your mother says
your brakes were on
and that you came
to a rolling stop,
so the question is--
she's making
an impassioned plea
that you made an attempt
to stop
and that
it was a close call.
Is that what you
were saying?
- That's what
I was saying, yes.
- So how do you wanna
find him?
Guilty or not guilty?
- Uh, I would
find him not guilty.
(attendees laughing)
- Surprise.
It's a big surprise,
Inspector Quinn.
- I'm totally shocked
on that ruling, Judge.
- All right, I asked for it,
so I guess you're gonna
be found not guilty.
Good luck to you.
- Thank you so much.
- All right, take care.
♪♪
(Judge Caprio)
- Daniel Ferreras.
Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
(Judge Caprio)
- You have a parking ticket
on Salisbury Street.
- Yeah.
- This is parking
in a prohibited area.
Now, listen, hold on a second.
All right, good.
We have two mics.
You are between
both of them.
Get to one or the other.
Get close,
get closer to the mic.
- Like that?
- Perfect.
Okay, what do you
wanna tell me?
You have a handicap placard.
- I missing
the ticket.
I... I'm no more
here for that.
But I go over to the...
to have
a handicap ticket.
Says $90.
It's too much for me.
- Mr. Ferreras,
a handicap...
placard allows you
to park in the handicap zone.
- Mm-hmm.
- It also allows you to park
at a parking meter
without putting
money in the meter.
- No have a meter,
nothing like that.
- I know.
It also allows
you to park
in a timed zone.
It does not allow
you to park
in a sign that
says "no parking."
Did you know that you could
not park there
with the placard?
- I only park there
30 seconds, sir.
- You were there 30 seconds?
- Yeah.
- All right, wait,
hold on for a minute.
- 30 seconds is up.
- Yes.
(Judge Caprio)
- You parked that far.
You get out of the car,
what did you do?
- I pick up
my daughter for the house
and outside, that's it.
- You went to your
daughter's house, all right...
and then you came
back out.
(Daniel)
- Yeah.
- And that took 30 seconds.
- From my car--
my car is 30--
(Judge Caprio)
- You took 30 seconds.
Right, you got out,
you ran
and got right back in.
Inspector Quinn, this guy's
the fastest guy in the country.
- I was gonna say, it takes
me about 30 seconds
to shut the car off,
open the car door,
shake it off
a little bit and get out.
- Inspector Quinn, he's got
a handicap placard.
You wanna give
him some leniency?
- Yes, Your Honor.
We wouldn't, uh...
We'll move to dismiss
with the warning,
advising him
about the legal spot.
I just wanna check the date
on that handicap.
- Mr. Ferreras, listen to me.
- Yes.
- All right,
just so you know...
... you said it took me
30 seconds
to go in the house...
see my daughter
and come back out.
You're handicapped.
- No, no, no, no,
no, to see my daughter--
- You've got a cane.
- I put daughter back
on fifth floor and go back.
- Yeah, I know, you went in,
you came back out
in 30 seconds.
- 30-45 seconds,
ah... something.
- You keep talking,
they're gonna take your
handicap placard away.
They're gonna say
you're pretty healthy.
You better be careful.
All right.
Based on the recommendation
of Inspector Quinn,
the matter is dismissed.
♪♪
According to your admission,
it was your party.
- I mean, I guess.
- You just told me,
you co-hosted it.
- Yeah, but it wasn't
just mine.
- Have you ever
been in a court?
- No, first time in my life,
and I am excited
about it.
Thank you very much!
Ordinary tissues left Dakota's
nose sore and red.
So Dad slayed the problem with
Puffs Plus Lotion, instead.
With lotion to soothe and
softness to please.
A nose in need deserves
Puffs, indeed.
♪♪
(Judge Caprio)
- Muammer Tukar.
Good morning, sir,
you are charged with...
- Good morning.
- ... parking overnight.
- Uh, yeah.
First of all, I am sorry
for my English.
Uh...
I am learn-- I am--
I am trying
to learn English.
If I say something wrong,
I am sorry for this.
- You can't say
anything wrong here.
(Muammer)
- Okay.
- Where are you from?
- Turkey.
- How long
have you been here?
- Uh, ten months here.
- You're doing
pretty good.
- Thank you very much.
- Yeah, what do you do?
Are you a student?
- I am-- I am...
studying in-- I am student
in Brown University,
and I am working in labs.
And today...
first time,
I park my car
in 3:00
and after
one and half hour...
when I...
when I come
to near my car,
I found a violation
parking ticket
and there is no sign
about the no parking here
because this is not own.
I just-- I want
to just study in lab two hours
but...
and there is no sign
about no parking
or no overnight parking.
- Okay.
Have you ever been
in a court in Turkey?
- No, first time here.
(Judge Caprio)
- First time in court?
- First time
in my life,
and I am excited about it.
- Well, we hope we give you
a favorable impression
of the United States
judicial system.
All right, so...
let me explain to you
what the situation is, okay?
Everything you said
is accurate.
Everything you said.
There are no signs
that say
you cannot
park overnight, all right?
And, plus, to complicate
matters more,
there's a sign saying
you can park during
certain hours,
and you were not parked
during those certain hours,
so, in your mind,
"I can park here."
Which makes sense to me.
Except that the city
has a...
a set of ordinances.
These are the city laws.
And in here it says
you cannot park overnight
in Providence.
So, before you came
from Turkey,
you were supposed
to read this book.
- Read all of that?
I have just two--
two months here.
(Judge Caprio chuckling)
- So...
it's a very
confusing thing.
People in Providence
know they can't,
but I don't think
it's fair for us
to charge you
for parking overnight,
when, number one,
you didn't know,
number two,
the sign was very misleading.
So that's the short version
of saying
that you won your case.
So when you
get back to Turkey,
you can say, "I was in
the United States,
"and I received
a summons to go to court,
and I fought the system
and I won."
- Am I won now?
(Judge Caprio)
- You win.
- Oh, thank you
very much.
(Judge Caprio chuckling)
Thank you.
- Good luck to you,
the matter is dismissed.
You did a-- you did
a wonderful job.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you again.
- As many of you know,
videos of our cases
have been watched
nearly two billion times
on social media platforms
such as YouTube
and Facebook.
Over half of these views
come from foreign countries.
Almost universally
the viewers comment
that they wished
the court proceedings
in their countries
were as fair
as the ones in our courtroom.
While not always perfect,
the United States
judicial system
is based on the premise
that everyone is innocent
until proven guilty.
That's not
the case everywhere.
I'm pleased that we were
able to demonstrate
that concept in person
to Mr. Tukar
in the hope
that he enjoys
the rest of his stay
in our great country.
Juliana Roland.
- Good morning, Your Honor.
(Judge Caprio)
- Good morning, Juliana.
Juliana, you have
a speeding ticket
on Chalkstone Avenue,
in a school zone.
- Yes.
(Judge Caprio)
- Is there anything
you wanna tell me about?
- Yes, Your Honor.
I'm here from
South Carolina.
I reside in South Carolina.
- In Lexington.
(Juliana)
- And-- I'm sorry.
- In Lexington, South Carolina.
- No, actually,
I'm in Blythewood.
(Judge Caprio)
- Oh--
- It was a rental vehicle.
- Oh.
- I have been
out of the state of Rhode Island
since 1994,
and I was back
visiting my dad--
88 years old.
He was entering
hospice that weekend.
And so...
I'm familiar with
the area.
I lived on Pembroke Avenue
just, you know, north of
Nathanael Greene Middle School.
I'm familiar with the area.
I was staying at a rental
property in Providence
and just picked up speed
going down that hill.
Didn't see the sign
for the school zone.
I know Nathanael Greene School
is there.
I've had one speed ticket
in my driving life, 1991,
on the New York State Thruway.
I had that dismissed
because I was a safe driver.
I just taught my
16-year-old to drive.
She was licensed last week.
So, I'm asking forgiveness,
if not leniency
for this because
I am a safe driver,
and... I'm certainly
guilty of the charge,
but, um...
- Well, you're one mile over
what I would charge ordinarily.
I have...
I have an issue,
not a problem.
I have an issue with that--
the location
of that particular mechanism,
because Chalkstone Avenue
is a hill going down...
- Yes, it is,
yes, it is.
- ... into Raymond Street,
and that's where
they've got the machine.
So you actually would
have to be
pumping the brakes
going down the hill
to be going...
to keep within
the speed limit,
and you were one over
what I usually charge,
so I'm gonna give you
a break.
- Thank you,
thank you, Your Honor.
- Is it your dad that's
going into hospice?
- He passed on June 12th,
so...
last time I saw him
but it was good to be here.
But nice gift.
But thank you for dismissing,
Your Honor.
I appreciate it.
- In memory
of your dad.
- Thank you, thank you--
thanks, Dad.
- Good luck.
You actually had
a pretty good morning.
You know that.
- Both tickets were not me,
and I have to pay
somebody else's mistake.
Yeah, it's a pretty
great morning.
(Judge Caprio)
- I think you better leave
before I change my mind.
Around here, nobody ever does
it.
I Didn't do it.
So when I heard they added Ultra
Oxi
to the cleaning power of Tide,
it was just what we needed.
Dad?
I didn't do it.
#1 stain and odor fighter, #1
trusted.
It's got to be Tide.
Stand up to Chronic
Migraine with BOTOX®.
What if you had fewer headaches
and migraines a month?
BOTOX® prevents
headaches and migraines
before they even start.
BOTOX® is for adults
with Chronic Migraine,
15 or more headache
days a month,
each lasting 4 hours or more.
BOTOX® injections take about
15 mins. in your doctor's office
and are covered
by most insurance.
Effects of BOTOX® may spread
hours to weeks after injection
causing serious symptoms.
Alert your doctor right away,
as difficulty swallowing,
speaking, breathing,
eye problems,
or muscle weakness
can be signs of a
life-threatening condition.
Side effects may
include allergic reactions,
neck and injection site pain,
fatigue, and headache.
Don't receive BOTOX® if
there's a skin infection.
Tell your doctor your
medical history, muscle or
nerve conditions,
and medications,
including botulinum toxins,
as these may increase the
risk of serious side effects.
With the BOTOX® Savings Program,
most people with
commercial insurance
pay nothing out of pocket.
Talk to your doctor and visit
BOTOXChronicMigraine.com
to enroll.
it's time for you to follow
"Caught in Providence"
on Facebook and Instagram.
Stay connected and get access
to show clips
and exclusive digital content.
(Judge Caprio)
- Aga Delgado.
This is a environmental summons.
MC59159.
Charges you with
a noise violation
where there was loud music
coming from your house
at 2:30 in the morning.
- Yeah.
(Judge Caprio)
- Where you having a party?
- Yeah, but this actually--
- What kind of a party
was it?
- This wasn't
actually my house,
so they kind of gave
it to me by accident.
They thought I lived there
because it was
my friend's house,
and I was there at the party
with everybody else,
but they assumed
I lived there,
so they gave me the fine.
The officer had
told me that
I could possibly
fight it or get it dismissed
since I am not a resident
at the house.
- So you were a guest.
- Yeah.
- According to
the police report,
the police spoke to you
and you said that
you were hosting
the welcome-back party.
Is that right?
- No.
Actually, I was
co-hosting with him,
so, yes, I was helping
and I was, like,
a part of it, but--
- So you were the organizer?
- No-- well, it was--
- You were hosting it,
you were the organizer.
- Yeah.
But, I mean, I guess
I really was the one
who took a fall for it.
- Yeah.
So, according to your admission,
it was your party.
- I mean... I guess.
- You just told me,
you co-hosted it.
- Yeah, but it wasn't
just mine.
- Was, uh...
Martin-- was Martin Severs
also--
- Yeah, he also got fined...
(Judge Caprio)
- He got one too.
- ... but his was
dismissed.
- Well, I'm not sure.
I didn't dismiss it.
- Yeah, I know,
I'm just saying.
- Inspector Quinn, you wanna
be heard on this?
- Your Honor,
based on the, uh...
the statements in the report,
um...
- Well, she was
a little disingenuous
when she first-- when she
first came out.
If you had just been honest
when you first came out
and said--
you know, you try
to pull the technical defense.
"Well, I was at my apartment,
I don't live there."
(Aga)
- No.
- You could have easily said,
"I co-hosted the party,
and I told the police
that and that's why I'm here."
- I mean, I was just--
- I know what you were
trying to do.
(Aga)
- Trying to say what
they had told me,
'cause they said that.
- I get it.
Inspector Quinn?
- Your Honor,
based on the report,
it would be $100
or she can have
a trial.
- You would've got
a much better disposition
if you had been honest
from the beginning.
Inspector Quinn
made a recommendation.
$100 fine or come back
and have a trial.
- I mean, I...
- The matter's set down
for trial.
Good luck.
If you wanna be trusted,
you must be honest.
If Ms. Delgado
had simply told me the truth
about her role in the party,
I would have been inclined
to dismiss the charges.
Thomas Jefferson once said,
"Honesty is the first chapter
in the book of wisdom."
It's also the best policy
for every situation
in life.
Including how
you behave in the courtroom.
♪♪
Tony Acevedo.
Tony, you have
three registrations.
- Hmm?
(Judge Caprio)
- Do you understand
what I just said?
- Three registrations?
- Yes.
Now, who's Maria--
- That's my mother,
sir.
(Judge Caprio)
- Valenzuela.
Are you here for her?
- Yes, sir.
- All right, she has
an overnight parking ticket
on Althea...
- Yes, sir.
- There's a $40 penalty.
I waived
the penalty.
- Thank you.
(Judge Caprio)
- So you just saved $40.
You got the first ticket
dismissed.
Now comes the bad news.
You have two
red-light violations.
One goes back
to last year
and one is...
just two weeks ago.
This is a ticket
on North Main and Branch
at 7:38 in the evening.
What's the time on that?
(man)
- .4, Your Honor.
(Judge Caprio)
- All right.
The next one is...
on Pleasant Valley
and Valley Street.
Is that him making
a right-hand turn?
(man)
- Yes, Your Honor.
That's no turn on red
at all.
(Judge Caprio)
- Was this during
the period of construction?
(man)
- Yes, Your Honor.
- I'm gonna find-- I'm gonna
dismiss that ticket
where the signs were confusing,
and it will be
$85 on the other.
This is gonna cost you
a total of $105.
You actually had
a pretty good morning.
You know that.
- Yeah.
Yeah, compared to that both--
both tickets were not me,
and I have to pay
somebody else's mistake.
Yeah, it's a pretty
great morning.
- I think you better leave
before I change my mind.
(man)
- I would.
♪♪
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50-85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
THE THREE WHAT?
THE THREE P'S?
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 54 AND I WAS
A SMOKER BUT QUIT.
ALEX, WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I'M 65, RETIRED,
AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
ALSO $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80
AND I'M ON A FIXED INCOME.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
THAT'S LESS THAN 35 CENTS A DAY.
YOU CANNOT BE TURNED DOWN
BECAUSE OF YOUR HEALTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
OPTIONS START AT $9.95 A MONTH,
PLUS, YOU GET A 30-DAY
MONEY BACK GUARANTEE.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
♪♪
(Judge Caprio)
- Daniel Capella.
- Good morning, Judge.
- Good morning, sir.
All right, you have
a parking meter violation.
- Yeah, it's from my wife.
Maria.
- You're throwing your
wife under the bus already.
- She goes to Providence
Power Yoga there and--
- She goes to yoga?
(Daniel)
- Yeah.
And she had to work
today, so...
- Oh, she's meditating.
- Does yoga,
does all those...
- Yeah, but I mean she must
be meditating now.
She sent you--
she sent you to court.
- I'm gonna have to meditate
for her.
(Judge Caprio)
- All right, what do you
wanna tell me on the merits
of the case?
- There's a parking lot there.
She said she always parks
in the parking lot,
so she doesn't understand.
- This one day she didn't
park in the parking lot
she got the ticket.
- Yeah.
- Now, the ticket
was 25,
you didn't pay it...
so it went
to 75.
But we're gonna
waive the penalties.
- Thank you.
- So you tell your wife
that you took
a really beating today
in front of the judge.
The judge
beat you down.
- I'm hobbling home.
- I don't want
you going home,
telling your wife
you paid $75
and try and get
reimbursed now.
- I wish.
- All right, $25.
- Thank you.
♪♪
UGH, ANOTHER DELAY...
BUT... YOU KEEP BOUNCING
LIKE I'M A BOUNCY CASTLE!
OH YEAH!! 5 STOPS, 0 LEAKS.
WE'RE CRUSHING THIS COMMUTE!
HUGGIES LITTLE MOVERS.
OUR BEST FITTING DIAPER
THAT FITS LIKE A HUGG.
HUGG ON.
Beauty editors have tried
everything.
In search of a whiter smile.
Their choice? Crest
3D Whitestrips.
Our exclusive whitening
formulation
safely whitens 25 times better*.
For a noticeably whiter, smile.
Trust America's #1
whitening treatment.
Crest 3D Whitestrips.
[SFX]
Red Rover, Red Rover
Send Reese's Pieces over
[SFX]
♪
Introducing new
Hershey's Milk Chocolate
and Reese's Pieces
Now in one bar
-Ah, the old crew!
Remember when we all used to go
to the cafeteria
and just chow down midday?
-You mean, like, lunch?
-Come on. Voted
"Most Likely to Help People
Save $668 When They Switch."
-At this school?
-Didn't you get caught
in the laminating machine?
-Ha. [ Sighs ]
-"Box, have a great summer.
Danielle."
Ooh.
Danielle, control yourself.
I'd like to slow it down here
with a special discount
for a special girl.
Danielle, this one's for you.
e a photographecial discount
for a special girl.
that shows this car
was parked right
in front of a sign
that says "tow zone,
no parking."
- He didn't see the sign?
(Judge Caprio)
I'm gonna send him-- I'm gonna
send him for an exam
to check his eyes.
The sign is right
in front of the car.
According to the photograph
I have,
he couldn't open
the door of his car
unless he saw
the sign.
(attendees laughing)
(man)
- Are you kidding?
(Judge Caprio)
- Here's your vehicle,
here's your vehicle,
here's vehicle and-- oh.
Do you still think you
stopped long enough?
- Yes.
Maybe not.
- Waive them.
- Why should I waive this
for your nephew
when you're
telling me that--
- Because he's nowhere
to be found.
- You're telling me
he's totally irresponsible.
On behalf of all the people
of Providence,
thank you for
paying your summons.