of it.
- She got
the parking tickets.
She had a slight stroke.
We didn't know that she
was gonna be admitted.
She's a fighter.
- I have a note,
Inspector Quinn,
from Ms. Yuridia.
"I'm not guilty,
and I don't have money."
- That gentleman had
the same note.
That gentleman
had the same note.
She had the same note.
(announcer)
- This is the courtroom
of Judge Frank Caprio,
where people and cases
are met with compassion.
A different kind of judge.
A courtroom
like no other.
This is "Caught in Providence."
(Judge Caprio)
- Yuridia Mesure.
- Good morning, sir.
(Judge Caprio)
- Good morning.
Oh, you're charged with...
failing to yield
the right of way
in a crosswalk.
- Yeah, I think
I not guilty
because I see
the-- the old woman
and I see her when she
wanna try to pass
but she is stopping,
she is stopping.
I think
she wanna pass.
That's why I'm going.
Not pulling--
and I'm sorry.
- I think you should plead
not guilty,
come back
and have a trial.
Can you do that?
- I-- when--
I come back?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry,
I can't come back
because I-- I lose hour
in my job
for I had
to come here.
I lose hour
in my job.
- What do you do?
- I am a CNA.
C-A-- CNA.
CNA, yeah.
I take care to the old people
at home, you know,
and I had to go later.
The people, they need me
in the morning.
- Do you have any children?
- Oh yes.
I have three--
three kids.
One is in college,
and I help
to the college,
and I pay the taxes,
I pay the house.
Everything.
It's not easy.
But I'm gonna try
doing the life the best I can.
- I have a note,
Inspector Quinn,
from Ms. Yuridia.
She, uh...
she failed
to come to court
and she got...
... she was violated
and as her excuse
to come back in
she says, "Please.
I'm not guilty,
and I don't have money."
- Your Honor, that gentleman
had the same note.
That gentleman
She had the same note.
- You have the same note?
- Oh, every day
when I wake up, Judge,
I put it on top of my wall
so my daughters
and my wife can read that.
(all chuckling)
- That's everybody
in this time.
- Exactly.
(Yuridia)
- It's hard.
The food is very expensive,
the tax--
everything is expensive.
And the kids,
when they grow up,
they eat more food.
- Oh, the kids
are sending you broke.
They've got big
appetites, huh?
- Yeah, exactly.
And they not give me
food stamp,
they not
give me nothing.
And I take nothing.
- Who does
the cooking, you?
- Yes, I cook.
I am a good cooking.
- What's the best
thing you make?
- Rice and beans and chicken.
- Rice, beans
and chicken.
- Yes, they like it.
- Inspector Quinn's mouth
is salivating.
Look at him.
(Inspector Quinn chuckling)
You like rice, beans
and chicken, Inspector Quinn?
- I have yet to
have it, Judge.
(Judge Caprio)
- I'm sure.
- Chicken I'm familiar with.
(Judge Caprio)
- I'm sure.
- And I start
to cook it when I--
I had nine years old
and I start to cook it.
- You started cooking
at nine?
- At nine years old.
- So you've been
cooking for five years?
- No, I...
(attendees laughing)
And a little kid
in my-- in my country.
(Judge Caprio chuckling)
- All right, you're
gonna pay $35 court cost.
- I pay right now,
no problem.
Thank you so much.
- Be careful.
(Yuridia)
- Yes.
- When you get to intersections,
if there's anybody
in the crosswalk, stop.
Even if they're
like one step
into the crosswalk, stop.
- Okay.
(Judge Caprio)
- They're out there.
- Okay, no more.
- No more, right?
All right.
♪♪
Gerald Lewis.
(man)
- Yeah, Mr. Lewis is present.
(Judge Caprio)
- Good morning, sir.
(Inspector Quinn)
- Get closer to the mic,
Mr. Lewis.
Thank you.
- Good morning, Your Honor.
- Mr. Lewis has been observed
speeding in a school zone
at 1:55 p.m.
Do you wanna be
heard, sir?
- Yes, if I may, Your Honor?
So I met Mr. Lewis
at Operation Stand Down
roughly a month ago,
and he explained
the situation to me.
Mr. Lewis served six years
in the Marines.
Directly following that,
he served one year
in the Army
and Operation Desert Storm,
and on the day
at hand,
Mr. Lewis was
actually heading to--
I'm sorry-- coming from
the VA hospital.
He had severe
pain his back
and was suffering from
a hernia
and they treat him
as well as they could
and they had put
a follow-up-date offer
for the treatment,
and on the way home
Mr. Lewis
passed through
the school zone
and that's where this
incident occurred.
In terms of the prior
court date that he missed,
Mr. Lewis confused the follow-up
appointment at the VA hospital
with the court date
given that, you know,
the incidences
were from the same day.
So, Your Honor,
with that being said,
you know, Mr. Lewis has
served our country,
and we ask you that,
with all that he's done,
that you dismiss this fine.
- All right, not with--
not withstanding that,
the motorist
is charged with doing
one mile over what the city
prosecutes for.
The city does not
prosecute if you're doing
11 miles over.
But there's-- the statute
provides that the city
has the discretion
to charge plus
or minus one mile per hour.
- I see.
- So I have routinely
dismissed cases
where the motorist
was doing 11 miles over.
He was doing 12 miles over,
so the issue that
I have to resolve in my mind
is does his service
to the country
and his...
position currently,
does that justify me
giving him a break
for one mile over?
And based on your argument,
I find that it does,
so the matter
will be dismissed.
- Great, thank you,
Your Honor.
- Okay, good job.
How long did you
prepare for this?
- Uh...
saying it to myself in
the mirror on the car ride here.
(attendees laughing)
- Well, you can do that
for traffic cases.
When you get to--
when you get to the felonies,
you better spend-- you better
spend some--
some time looking
in the mirror for a week before.
(attendees laughing)
Good luck, you did
a good job.
- Thank you very much,
Your Honor, appreciate it.
(man)
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- I was really drunk.
- Did you speak to the police
when they came?
- If I did,
I don't remember.
- You allow her to use
the vehicle occasionally?
- Sometimes.
- All right.
- When she's good.
- And I'm always good.
Reese's eggs are back
and we hid them
somewhere you'll never find...
Sike! We put them everywhere.
Grocery stores and
supermarkets, gas stations,
and chiropractor's offices,
bowling alleys,
and grocery stores,
which we already mentioned...
Not Sorry, Reese's.
CHARMIN ULTRA SOFT!
IT'S SOFTER THAN EVER.
CHARMIN ULTRA SOFT IS SOFTER
THAN EVER SO IT'S HARDER TO
RESIST.
OKAY, THIS IS GETTING
A LITTLE WEIRD
ENJOY THE GO WITH CHARMIN
My name is
Elaine Barber,
and I'm a
five-year cancer survivor.
Surviving for five years
is a big deal.
I had so many people at CTCA
helping me find a way to go
through the treatments.
The reality of cancer is
not everybody survives.
At CTCA,
they have a huge
celebrate life event.
That was amazing
because the whole day
was about all of the survivors.
I'm excited about my future.
Learn more at
cancercenter.com/Philadelphia.
I'm excited about my future.
Z35WHZ Z16FZ
Y35WHY Y16FY
♪♪
(Judge Caprio)
- Kimberly Allovera.
- Good morning.
- This your lawyer?
- My husband.
(Judge Caprio)
- Oh, your husband.
Okay.
Uh, why don't you guys
get two separate mics, okay?
I know-- I know you're
a very close family
and you wanna
stay close together, right.
(Judge Caprio laughing)
All right, now,
I'm gonna take a guess.
You were driving
the vehicle.
- She was.
- Inspector Quinn,
I started off wrong.
(Kimberly laughing)
You-- you allow her to use
the vehicle occasionally?
- Sometimes.
- It's a pretty--
- When she's good.
- And I'm
always good.
- Pretty fancy SUV.
Let's see.
You're charged with
parking in a prohibited area
on Fifth Street.
- Yes.
My grandmother--
- I mean, I know why
you're here, incidentally.
- I don't know why either.
(Judge Caprio)
- I know why you're here.
You're here to pay,
you're here to pay.
- To pay, yeah.
- That's why you're here.
Who's gonna pay,
you or him?
- He is.
(Judge Caprio)
- She does the crime
and I pay for it.
(Kimberly laughing)
- I swear, she's completely
relaxed, she don't care.
- Hey, that was
the arrangement.
(Judge Caprio)
- All right, what happened?
- That's the benefits
of being married.
- How many children
do you have?
- We have two now.
- Yeah.
Well, you're charged with
parking in a prohibited area
on Fifth Street.
That's up near
Miriam Hospital.
What do you wanna
tell me about it?
- Well, it was a-- it was
a very busy day that day.
I was actually
following my mother,
because I didn't know how to get
to the hospital--
- Oh, now you're throwing
your mother under the bus.
- I know.
I have to because
it's part of--
I don't understand
why I got the ticket
and nobody else did.
- All right.
- But my grandmother had
been admitted the night before,
so I was going to help
my mother out.
So I followed her
into two parking lots.
There was no place to park.
Valet was out
in the street.
So we parked on the street
I followed her to.
We parked there,
there was a delivery truck
in front of us,
we went in,
she asked the valet
if it was okay to be
parked there.
He said it was okay
as long as it was
less than two hours.
So I made sure it was
less than two hours,
but when I came out,
I had a ticket.
Her car was still there,
she did not have a ticket.
- Well, I have a photograph
of the area
and a photograph of your car,
and there is a delivery
truck in front of you and--
- Yeah, I think it was only
within ten minutes
I got that ticket,
according to the stamp
that was on it,
the time stamp.
- And next to the delivery truck
is a pole with signs on it,
which are not
visible in the photograph.
So what do you think,
Inspector Quinn?
- Your Honor, the signs
on the pole say,
"No parking anytime.
Deliveries
between 8:00 and 4:00."
- Does it really?
- Your Honor, there's no way
I could've read that sign.
(Kimberly laughing)
The photo the city
provided, Your Honor,
does not allow me the ability
to read the times on the sign.
- Okay.
Okay, so you're following
your mother to the hospital
because your grandmother was
in the hospital, right?
You asked the valet,
"Where can I park?"
He says, "Park over there."
You said to him,
"Are you sure?"
He says, "Sure I'm sure"--
he don't care.
- Right.
(Judge Caprio)
- He don't care.
He figures, I'm gonna
get rid of her, right?
I've got
other stuff to do.
Park anywhere you want.
And then you drag
your husband into court.
- Yeah.
He wanted to come.
- You guys get along
pretty good.
You're recently married?
- No.
37 years.
- How many?
- 37.
- 37 years?
- I feel your pain.
Same thing.
- It's been good
so far.
(Judge Caprio)
- I'm gonna ask you a question.
- Okay.
- This is a family joke
and I'll explain it
after I finish.
How many years
have you been happily married?
(Kimberly laughing)
You don't
have to answer.
- 30.
- You don't have to--
you don't have to answer.
- Well, it's like a hill,
up and down.
- It's up and down,
it's like this.
Peaks and valleys.
- Yeah.
(Judge Caprio)
- Okay.
That's life,
life is peaks and valleys.
But my wife and I have
been married
50 years,
and every time...
- God bless you.
- ... we meet people,
I'll introduce people,
and I'll say-- I want
to introduce my--
they say, "Oh, how long
have you been married?"
I say, "Oh, we've been
happily married for five years."
(Kimberly laughing)
And they say, "Oh, is this
your second or third wife?"
"No, no, no,
no, no."
(Inspector Quinn chuckling)
Inspector Quinn,
who is the prosecuting officer,
said he can't read the sign.
So if he can't read the sign,
the city can't prove its case.
If the city can't prove
its case,
the matter's
gonna be dismissed.
You just saved
30 bucks.
- Thank you, I appreciate it.
(Judge Caprio)
- Take her to breakfast.
- Now go for the $100 breakfast.
(Kimberly laughing)
- Thank you.
(man)
- Have a good day.
♪♪
(Judge Caprio)
- Julio Franco.
- Good morning, Your Honor.
(Judge Caprio)
- Good morning, Mr. Franco.
You have two parking tickets.
They're both
on Blackstone Street.
Is there anything you wanna
tell me about these?
- Um...
(Judge Caprio)
- Speak into the mic, please.
- I'm here on behalf
of Sandra Desisto.
Um...
she got the parking tickets.
She had a slight,
uh... stroke.
We didn't know that
she was gonna be admitted,
and we were there
overnight.
Actually, we were
there two days.
When I came out,
the car had the boot on it.
It was $368 to have the boot
taken off.
I thought that
by paying to have
the boot taken off that
the tickets would be included.
- Well, they were...
The tickets up to that time
were included.
When, uh, when was
the boot taken off?
What day was that
taken off?
- The same day.
(Judge Caprio)
- What date, do you know?
- August 7th.
- You paid to have
the boot removed,
and you paid
for all the tickets?
- Yes.
- I think you
suffered enough.
- Thank you.
- How's she doing?
- Um, she's doing
all right.
She's having
therapy and, um...
she's a fighter.
- Well, she's got
a good friend with you.
She's lucky to have you.
- Thank you.
- All right, good luck.
- The matter's dismissed.
- Thank you very much.
(Judge Caprio)
- This was at 10:41
in the evening.
- Now, did I have
a car like that?
What year is that?
- I came here to ask
the questions,
not to answer them.
Emerge Restored,
Replenished,
Fortified.
Emerge everyday with Emergen-C.
Packed with B vitamins,
Electrolytes, Antioxidants,
Plus more vitamin C than
10 oranges.
Why not feel this good
every day?
Emerge and See.
My digestive system used
to make me feel sluggish
But now, I take
Metamucil every day.
It traps and removes the
waste that weighs me down,
So I feel lighter.
Try Metamucil, and begin to
feel what lighter feels like.
Free!
Free, free free.
♪
That's right. TurboTax Free
is free. Free, free free free.
e has ruled that
it's time for you to follow
"Caught in Providence"
on Facebook and Instagram.
Stay connected and get access
to show clips
and exclusive digital content.
(Judge Caprio)
- Bernadette Ortiz.
Okay, Bernadette, you're
charged with, uh...
loud music
coming from your home...
at 3:30 in the morning.
Was you having
a party?
- I was having
a get-together.
- What was the occasion?
- Just celebrating.
- A bunch of friends.
- Just a little get-together,
people over.
(Judge Caprio)
- How many people in the house?
- 12 or so.
- Well, you have
two choices.
You can pay a...
you can plead
guilty today
and I'll impose a fine,
or you can come back
and have a trial.
Is there anything
you wanna tell me about it?
- It was just a simple--
we was drinking,
I got drunk,
and... I blacked out.
Don't remember
much of it.
- You blacked out?
- Yeah, I don't remember
the cops coming and stuff, so--
(Judge Caprio)
- But did you--
- I was really drunk.
- Did you speak to the police
when they came in?
- If I did,
I don't remember.
- Oh, you don't remember
what you said.
'Cause there's
a police report on this
and...
(Judge Caprio laughing)
I'm not gonna read
the police report.
Okay.
I'm sure you probably said,
"Listen, sir, I'm sorry.
"You know, we're just having
some friends getting together,
"and I realize, Officer,
you have a tough job
and please
show us some mercy."
I think-- I think that's
what you said
to the police officer, right?
- I hope so.
- Something like that.
What do you think,
Inspector Quinn?
Is that what she said?
- If you had to read that
report, it sounds like--
(Judge Caprio)
- We're not reading the report.
We're not gonna-- we're not
gonna do that to her.
- Your version of that
report, I have yet to read that.
- She comes across,
she's very honest,
she said, "Listen,
I had too much to drink.
"I had some friends,
the cops came.
"Maybe I said some
stuff that was inappropriate
but that's not really me."
- Right.
- Is that what
you wanted to say?
- Perfect, it's on point.
- All right.
Now, that's what you wanted--
now, what are you really
thinking?
- I was wondering
what I really said.
(Bernadette laughing)
- Well, there's a $500
fine here,
so how do you plead:
guilty or not guilty?
- I would say guilty with
an explanation,
which I just gave, so--
- Yeah.
I don't know,
Inspector Quinn.
I think we have to fine her.
But I just dropped
one of the zeros,
so it's gonna
cost you $50.
- Thank you.
- And--
- I thought you dropped the zero
after the decimal point.
(attendees laughing)
- Now, there were
13 people at the party, right?
- Yeah.
We-- we was all
just having fun.
It got out of hand,
I guess,
'cause after a few drinks--
- I think you better-- I think
you better call them up
and tell them--
- I'm gonna start charging
$25 a head
or something from them.
- It's a $50 fine, right,
so call them up
and tell them they owe $4 each.
They all have to participate
in the fine, right?
- Yes.
- Okay, good luck to you.
- Thank you.
- When you come to court,
you are required
to tell the truth,
the whole truth, and nothing
but the truth.
But nowhere do we
ask that you over share.
- I was eight months pregnant
and I had to pee.
- Yeah, I was over
my girlfriend's house.
- And I just had my--
some surgery,
my fingers amputated.
- While we appreciated
Ms. Ortiz's honesty
when she admitted that
she got blackout drunk,
she could have simply said
that she was overserved;
a phrase that I'm occasionally
required to employ.
Hey, it happens.
Happy birthday,
Bernadette,
and next year
might I recommend
water, wine, water, wine,
and you'll be fine.
Pro tip.
No charge.
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50-85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
THE THREE WHAT?
THE THREE P'S?
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 54 AND I WAS
A SMOKER BUT QUIT.
ALEX, WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I'M 65, RETIRED,
AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
ALSO $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80
AND I'M ON A FIXED INCOME.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
THAT'S LESS THAN 35 CENTS A DAY.
YOU CANNOT BE TURNED DOWN
BECAUSE OF YOUR HEALTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
OPTIONS START AT $9.95 A MONTH,
PLUS, YOU GET A 30-DAY
MONEY BACK GUARANTEE.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
♪♪
(Judge Caprio)
- Cornelius Adams.
Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
- Okay, you have five
different registrations.
- Yeah, I got three cars.
- You're a three-car
household, huh?
- Yeah, well, my--
(Judge Caprio)
- What, do you use one
for different days?
- No, no, my son
has one, I have one,
and then my girl has one.
- Oh, I see.
- So they all registered
my car, so...
when I came to court
I found out who
the culprits were, so--
- On the Chevrolet-- who
drives the Chevrolet?
(Cornelius)
- That would be my son.
- How old is your son?
- My son is 20.
He's in college right now
in New Mexico.
- Mexico?
- Yeah, he plays football.
- Well, I can see where
he got his
athletic ability
from, looking at you.
(Cornelius)
- Yeah, I went to--
- His mother.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I went
to Mount Pleasant.
I graduated from
over there '89.
(Judge Caprio)
- Yeah.
- And did you play
sports after that?
- Of course, at URI.
That was
back in... '90.
- I think you should've
stuck it out.
You probably could've
played for the Patriots.
Look at the size of you.
- Ah, prob-- most like--
I think my son--
my son, most likely.
- Okay, on the red-light ticket
we're gonna take a look at it.
- Okay.
- This was at 10:41
in the evening.
- Now, did I have
a car like that?
What year is that?
- I came here to ask
the questions,
not to answer them.
- All right, yeah,
Your Honor, yeah, just curious.
- I'm gonna dismiss
the parking ticket overnight.
It's gonna cost you $85
for the red light.
- Shh...
- Well, you got
a good deal here.
See the clerk.
- Yes.
Can I get a little time
to come back
and bring the money
if I gotta pay, though?
- Work it out-- work it out
with Alyssa.
- All right, all right.
- Good luck.
(Cornelius)
- Appreciate it.
Got it?
Got it.
Nooooo...
Quick, the Quicker Picker Upper!
Bounty picks up messes quicker
and is 2x more absorbent.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker
Upper.
met-- I met your son
eight years ago
when he was
running for governor.
- See, what you're
supposed to do is,
before I make a decision,
you're supposed to really
butter me up.
So before I made
a decision on that case,
you're supposed to say,
"I met your son,"
and then you--
whatever you wanna tell me.
You know, "I can't stand him,"
or "he's a good guy."
Something like that.
- It was just a pleasure.
- Thank you for
those compliments.
Very nice of you.
(man)
- Are you kidding?
- After the cops came...
- (Judge Caprio) Yeah?
- ...my brother got in a fight
with one of the cops.
- Ohh!
- Hence the ticket.