so they had to remove
the bone, like, the skull.
- Francesca?
- Yes.
- If I followed normal
protocol on this,
you would end up with no car.
(announcer)
- This is the courtroom
of Judge Frank Caprio
where people and cases
are met with compassion.
A different kind of judge.
A courtroom
like no other.
This is
"Caught in Providence."
- Who's Mr. Holder?
- Uh, this is Mr. Holder,
Your Honor.
- And, and are you
here with him?
- Uh, yes, I'm his counselor
at the Riverwood program.
- Okay, and who's gonna
do the speaking?
- Uh, I am
at Mr. Holder's request.
- All right, what do you wanna
tell me about this?
- Uh, basically, he received
the ticket on Sunday morning.
Uh, it's not at all
his first parking--
- Saturday.
- I'm sorry?
Saturday morning, I'm sorry.
It's not at all
his first ticket.
- He's had, he's had 31 tickets.
- Uh, obviously,
I'm his counselor
for significant reasons.
At the same time, it's something
that we're working on
engagingly with Mr. Holder.
And, uh, truthfully, speaking,
the tickets are becoming
further and further apart.
Uh, he happened to have
been parked across from
Burnside Park
in front of the old
Bank of America building.
On this particular morning,
uh, he was attending
a church service.
Sometimes he goes there also
to meet up with his daughter
who's currently
in a homeless situation.
Uh, so we are hoping that, uh,
Your Honor could find the reason
hopefully to waive this and know
that we're working actively
in terms of keeping
this from happening.
- Is he homeless now?
- Uh, currently speaking,
he lives with his father
at an assisted living residence
in East Providence.
But, uh, actually, we have
an appointment next week
with the Gateway group to
hopefully line up housing--
affordable housing
in North Providence.
- Tell me about the program.
I don't know what
the program is about.
- Um, we're
a social services agency.
We're under the Horizon Group.
We have two locations.
One in Providence,
one in Warren, Rhode Island,
uh, you know,
in the East Bay area.
Uh, Mr. Holder's been a longtime
client of ours and whatnot.
I've been working
as his counselor for about
the last nine months.
- What's the name
of the program?
- Riverwood, one word.
(Judge)
- Are you familiar with that?
(Inspector Quinn)
- No, but I am familiar
with Horizon,
uh, I have heard of that.
- It's basically human services
and social work,
primarily the role
of the Providence program
is to provide, uh...
affordable housing
for low-income individuals.
- Based on your representation,
I'm gonna dismiss it.
- Thank you.
- But I want Mr. Holder
to know that...
this doesn't give you a license
in the future to say,
"It's okay, I'll bring
my counselor down
and I can get out
and get way with it", okay?
I'm doing this based
on his representation.
Do you understand that?
You explain it to him
when he gets out
'cause he's homeless, okay?
All right.
- It's our intention to avoid it
if at all possible.
Thank you, Your Honor.
- Okay.
- I'm just trying to see
if he gives me attitude.
- Despite what
you may be thinking,
I believe this motorist
actually made
two wise choices in court today.
The first having his social
worker speak for him.
Can you imagine what
would've happened if he had
opened his mouth?
I think he'd still be enjoying
the hospitality
of one of our local
correctional institutions.
The second is that
he waited until he passed
Inspector Carignan before
he disrespected the Judge.
Trust me, that may have been
the wisest move of his life.
- Anthony Michael Giacobbi.
Good morning, Mr. Giacobbi.
- Good morning, sir.
- What do your friends call you?
They call you Tony?
They call you A.M.?
What do they call you?
- I can't say what they call me.
(all laughing)
- I expected
that kind of an answer.
You're from, uh...
Where are you from, Nevada?
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah?
What are you doing
in Rhode Island?
- What am I doing?
I moved back here, stupidly.
(courtroom laughs)
- Are you calling me stupid?
- I was thinking about it,
but I...
(all laughing)
Listen, I'm gonna
tell you something.
That's not nice.
Mr. Giacobbi, uh...
You're charged with going
through red light on Allens
Avenue and Terminal Street.
We watching these today?
We should watch it.
- Yes.
- All right.
Here's what we're gonna do,
Mr. Giacobbi.
I'm gonna watch it.
Now there are two lines
on Allens Avenue.
There are two stop lines.
If you are past
the first stop line
when the light turns red,
I'll dismiss it.
If you're not past it,
it's gonna cost you 85 bucks.
We're gonna take a look at it.
Look up here.
(Inspector Quinn)
- It's already red, Judge.
Show the time light.
It was r red
for 16.2 seconds, Judge.
- If I look at this...
I look at this every day and...
I'm supposed to know that when
the light clicks three times
that it's red.
Supposed to know that.
I think we're all supposed
to know that.
So, they send me this kind
of a video in a court of law.
I can't tell what color
the light is.
I know it changed three times,
Inspector Quinn,
but it went from white
to white to white.
- No, it didn't change at all,
Judge.
It stayed... red according
to the notice.
But according to the video,
I agree with you, Judge.
I couldn't determine...
- No.
The answer is
I am not convinced
by clear and convincing
evidence.
They didn't present clear
and convincing evidence to me
that the light was red.
I never saw red on the screen.
I saw it all white.
I know it changed three times,
but I don't know
when it changed three times
what color it was.
That's a very long story.
But the result is that
I'm gonna dismiss the case
because the city has failed to
prove by clear and convincing
evidence that you went
through a red light.
Now is there anything
you wanna say?
- Thank you.
- Oh.
(laughter)
He's never told me
what your friends call you.
What do you friends call you?
They call you Tony?
They all you Anthony?
What do they call you?
- (bleep) hole.
(laughter)
- His middle name.
- Thank you, sir.
- Well,
I guess we had it coming.
The Judge did ask him
three times
what his friends called him.
Based on his response,
we know he wasn't lying.
He really is an (bleep) hole.
- Jose Horentos.
- Good morning, Your Honor.
- You had a parking ticket
on Thayer Street, sir.
- Yes, um...
That day I wasn't
driving the car.
I was just getting
out of the hospital
'cause I had brain surgery.
And my son literally parked
at the corner of CVS
and I got in the car.
And the lady said,
"You know, you can't park.
There's a fire hydrant."
And I said, "All right,
I understand, I had brain
surgery, I had my helmet on."
And then she says, "Yeah, sure."
She didn't really believe me.
I got in the car, and then,
you know, we left.
And then I got the mail
and the ticket.
She didn't even give
us a ticket on the windshield
or anything.
- All right, case is dismissed.
- I appreciate it,
Your Honor, thank you.
- Good luck.
How are you feeling?
I can't hear you.
Speak into the mic.
- I had brain cancer surgery
and then it got infected.
So they had to remove the bone,
like, the...
the skull of my head... Yeah.
- The skull?
So, that's why you're
wearing a helmet?
- Helmet, yes.
- Yeah?
- So hopefully in October,
I'm good.
- Okay, we're rooting for you.
Good luck.
- I appreciate it.
Thank you.
- I got divorced from him maybe
about six or seven years ago.
- Yeah.
- Right before he went to
federal prison for 15 years.
- You're telling me all these
bad things about him,
but when he comes in,
you let him use the car.
- You're telling me all these
bad things about him,
It's just a cough.
Yeah right.
And the earth is flat.
Ahhh!!
Treat your cough seriously
with Robitussin CF Max.
Nothing lasts longer
and treats more symptoms for
your cough, cold and flu.
Robitussin. Because
it's never just a cough.
-We're doing karaoke later,
and you're gonna sing.
-Jamie, this is your house?
-I know, it's not much,
but it's home.
Right, kids?
-Kids?
-Papa, Papa!
-[ Laughs ]
-You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
-Oh, yeah.
-This one is tiny like a child.
-Yeah, she is.
Oh, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most --
a home and auto bundle
from Progressive.
-Oh, sweetie,
please, play for us.
-Oh, no, I couldn't.
-Please.
-Okay.
[ Singing in Spanish ]
- Kathy Acosta.
Kathy, you have
two red light violations.
- Yeah.
I-- they-- it wasn't me driving.
- Who drives?
- It was my ex-husband.
He lives in Puerto Rico.
And the first one that he got,
he said he paid it.
Now I get a second
one in the mail.
And I'm furious.
- Are...
- Um...
- Are you divorced
from this guy?
- Yes, I am.
- When did you get divorced?
- Uh, well...
- A year ago? Two years ago?
Six months ago? When?
- Oh, I got divorced from him
maybe about
six or seven years ago.
- Yeah.
- Right before he went to
federal prison for 15 years.
- Well...
- Just to explain
what a good citizen he is.
- Well, the fact of the matter
is that the ticket
was just issued last month.
- Yeah.
He just left last month.
- Oh, he's your ex-husband...
- The first one...
- He's your ex-husband but you
still let him use your car.
- Well, I try to be fair.
- I mean, you're telling me
all these bad things
about him
but when he comes in,
you let him use the car.
- True, true.
That it... That's against me
for being foolish.
- No, it's not against you.
I'm just trying to figure
something out.
- It's because
we have a child together.
She's grown now, but...
- Let's take a look at it.
Here he goes right through
the light, he don't care.
Let's look at the other one.
(man)
- Red, there he goes.
- Yeah, that was a close one.
All right, lights, please.
Kathy, I think you sufuffer
from having a big heart.
I think you're just
too, uh, kind and...
- Suffered for a long time.
- Yeah?
- I paid my dues.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna dismiss
one of these because
you're paying.
- Yeah, but what I wanted to do
was to have him
pay both of them.
- Well, here's...
- But on his license
in Puerto Rico.
- Kathy, when you
receive these summonses,
on the back of the summons,
if you had told us
who was driving the car
then he would
be held responsible.
You didn't do that.
And the time
for that has passed.
So, it's too late to do that.
I would love to help you.
If I could do it I would do it.
But it has no, no effect.
If you had done it originally,
then we would have notified
the authorities there,
and he would've had a problem.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Lesson learned.
- Good luck to you.
♪♪
Jennifer Cruz.
Jennifer, get close to the mic.
- Good morning, Your Honor.
- What is your daughter's name?
- Marleni.
- What is it?
- She's very well-behaved.
- Thank you.
- How old are you, honey?
- I'm five years old.
- Five?
- Do you wanna come up here?
- Do you wanna
go up there?
(Inspector Quinn)
- Come up.
Okay, you have three tickets.
- Yes, I don't wish to contend.
I was just hoping
that you could, um,
the late fees, I was hoping
that you could...
take those off
and I'd pay the tickets.
- Okay.
Do you have an excuse
for any of these tickets?
- Um, I know that the, um,
the one on South Main Street,
I had put just,
um, one quarter in
because I was just
going to get my BCI.
And there was, like,
20 people in there waiting
so they were backed up.
- I want-- I wanna
show you something
so don't leave yet, okay?
- Okay.
- Hold on.
Okay, you're gonna help me
out with these, okay?
- Okay.
- All right, now,
I got three choices.
And these are the three choices.
- I can charge your mom
number one is $50, right?
And number two...
is $100.
And number three is $150.
So, should I charge her number
one, number two or number three?
- Number one, Leni.
- Oh, no, no, no...
(laughter)
Oh, you can't,
you can't help her.
I'm gonna change
it around now, okay?
- Okay.
- What do you think?
- Number one.
- Number one?
Is that because your mom
helped you out?
It is, huh?
I think she cheated a little
bit, what do you think?
- Yes?
- Oh, she thinks you cheated.
Okay, well...
I asked you to help me
so I'm gonna take your
recommendation.
It's gonna be $50, okay?
- Okay.
- All right,
thanks for helping me out.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- Your fine was...
(clears throat)
$980.
- Yes.
- What do you wanna say?
- First, I'm terribly sorry.
- No, I don't wanna hear that.
♪ ♪
Let's face it,
the world
could use some warmth.
♪ ♪
UGH, ANOTHER DELAY...
BUT... YOU KEEP BOUNCING
LIKE I'M A BOUNCY CASTLE!
OH YEAH!! 5 STOPS, 0 LEAKS.
WE'RE CRUSHING THIS COMMUTE!
HUGGIES LITTLE MOVERS.
OUR BEST FITTING DIAPER
THAT FITS LIKE A HUGG.
HUGG ON.
♪♪
Shorten your cold
by almost half
with Cold-EEZE®
Lozenges.
Cold-EEZE® can shorten
your cold by 42%.
It releases zinc ions
that some scientists
believe inhibit cold
viruses from replicating.
Try Cold-EEZE® Lozenges.
This is Secret Clinical.
This is not Secret Clinical.
Secret Clinical.
Not Secret Clinical.
A single use of Secret Clinical
is the same as two uses
of the leading invisible solid.
Twice the sweat protection,
Secret Clinical.
I had been diagnosed with
Stage 4 prostate cancer.
I serve in the general
assembly and we work
together across the aisle
to get things done.
And that's the way
it is at CTCA.
What Fred needed was
a management team.
Not just to have a
long-term strategy for
quantity of life, but
also an active strategy
for quality of life.
My PSA is under control.
CTCA gave me an
opportunity to accomplish
my goals and my dreams.
Learn more at
cancercenter.com/philadelphia
Appointments available now.
- Francesca?
- Hello.
- Your motor vehicle
has been booted.
- Yes.
- And you came to court on...
- Last year sometime.
- November of last year.
- Yes.
- Your fine was...
(clears throat)
$980.
- Yes.
I missed my-- okay.
- I told you
at that point
that I would release the boot
if you paid $20 a week...
- Yeah, that was
on my mom's car.
- For 30 weeks.
- Yes.
- Which is $300.
- Mm-hmm.
- So, I... said to you
that you could
pay the $20 a week for 15 weeks
and that if you did that
that I would dismiss
the entire balance of $660.
- Yes.
- You solemnly promised
that you would do that.
Absolutely,
thank you, Judge.
I will do that every week,
and I told you at that point
that we have not changed
our phone number here.
That if there was any reason
why you couldn't pay,
that you should call.
So, you made three payments
and never made another payment.
- I made more than three
payments.
- You made three payments.
So...
- Some of them were for 40.
And a few, like,
I think, for 60.
- You made three payments.
- In January, I got evicted from
my apartment, so after that...
- We haven't changed
our phone number.
- Okay... I'm sorry.
- So, all I'm telling
you is that
any representations
you made to the court today
I will be suspect
whether or not you will
keep your word because
you broke your word last time
after I bent over backwards
to give you a big break.
- So, what do you wanna say?
- First, I'm terribly
sorry and...
- No, I don't wanna hear that.
- Okay, well, in January,
I was-- I got evicted
from my place, and I was going
through a lot with my two kids.
- Listen, the fact that-- that
fact of the matter is that
if the car wasn't booted,
you wouldn't come down here.
You know the car was booted.
You know you were saving $620.
All you had to do was
pay the $20 a week.
You didn't do it.
You didn't do it,
you didn't call.
We understand.
People call all the time
and say, "Listen, something
happened, I can't pay."
We say, "Okay."
But we... we, at least--
They at least contact us.
But you just didn't contact us.
I don't know what you thought.
- After speaking with the Judge,
I wanted 400 in order
to release the boot.
There's a little
issue with that.
So, the Judge has said we're
gonna release the boot on $200.
And we'll put you back
on the $20 payment plan.
But I can assure you this.
If you don't adhere to the $20
payment plan a week,
next time you're not
gonna get the car back
unless it's a substantial amount
of money back for the city.
So the Judge, once again,
is bending completely over.
Last time,
he bent over backwards.
Right now he's head
over heels, so...
You gotta help
the court a little bit.
- Francesca?
- Yes.
- If I followed normal
protocol on this
you would end up
with no car.
Because if I don't
release the boot,
the car will get towed.
If the car gets towed,
you will then owe
all this money which is $1,080.
And then you will
owe the tow company
approximately $100 for the tow.
And then they charge
storage every day.
- Yes.
- So, effectively,
what I would be doing is
I would be taking
your car away from you.
I know you have children.
I don't wanna do that.
But I want you
to show some good faith.
- Yes.
- Okay, so I'm trying
to help you.
Now all I'm asking
is that you help yourself.
- Thank you.
- Inspector Quinn
explained to you
I'm gonna hold back
on having the car towed.
I'm gonna leave the boot
on until tomorrow.
I will be here tomorrow.
- Okay.
- Come in and hopefully
we can get this resolved.
Do you understand that?
- Yes.
- All right, good luck to you.
- Thank you.
- Gregory Gautier.
Good morning, sir.
- Good morning, Your Honor.
- You have four tickets, sir.
Uh... let's see.
Two on Westminster...
Exchange and Atwells Avenue.
- The three most
current ones, um,
is parked around the streets
that surround One Financial
Plaza which is where I work.
I'm guilty.
I had to run in, run out.
Sometimes I got delayed, so I'm
guilty at that, Your Honor.
- All right.
- I was wondering
if I could, uh...
- Waive the penalties?
- Yes, sir, yes, Your Honor.
- I think we can do that.
- The one on Atwells Avenue
goes back a few years.
And it was, uh, in December.
And the, um, it was, uh,
around Christmastime.
I was up there for lunch
and I didn't see the...
- Where did we have lunch?
- I-- what did I have?
- No, where?
- Oh, Venda Ravioli, Your Honor.
- Do you remember what you had?
- Uh...
No, I do not.
- Judge, if he said corned beef,
I was gonna think he was lying.
(all laughing)
- Yeah, that got some pretty
good dishes up there.
- Uh...
- You know, I mean, they make
the ravioli--
They're homemade.
I was born and raised
in that area.
And many times
people will say to me,
"What's the best Italian
restaurant up there?"
And the answer is there
were several good ones.
I have a personal
preference which I,
I don't feel at liberty
to, uh, disclose.
But Italians really
gauge a restaurant on...
on their pasta and...
And they really-- and then
it goes further than that.
They gauge it on their gravy.
Now Italians call red sauce,
gravy, right?
Everyone else,
when I talk about gravy,
they think I'm talking
about something you put
on chicken or something
over mashed potatoes.
Right, Inspector Quinn?
- No, Your Honor.
I'm familiar with
the red gravy also.
- It's obvious.
(laughter)
(chuckling)
- All right.
I'm aware of the decorations up
there at Christmastime.
As a matter of fact...
I've often wondered why more
tickets don't go out there
on the Christmas vacation
'cause they do have
decorations all over the place.
All right, so I'm gonna
dismiss that ticket, it's $90.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- All right, good luck.
All right, so I'm gonna
dismiss that ticket, it's $90.
Got it?
Got it.
Nooooo...
Quick, the Quicker Picker Upper!
Bounty picks up messes quicker
and is 2x more absorbent.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker
Upper.
If only there was a place nearby
you could get one of these.
Or these.
Good thing they're
sold literally
everywhere business is done.
I'm pretty sure you could
buy them at a bank.
Not Sorry.
Reese's.
So, when you leave, you tell him
that I was gonna fine him
the full amount and that
your argument was
so compelling, right,
that you beat me down,
and I dismissed the case.
So, that he will owe you, right?
Should buy you a nice gift.
You can tell him when you leave.
- Okay.
- That way you can
exaggerate, okay?
Are you kidding?
>> TODAY, ON "FACE THE TRUTH."
>> WHAT KIND OF DRUGS DOES USE?
>> PCP.
>> A HISTORY OF ADDICTION IS
TEARING THE FAMILY APART.
>> YOU ALSO THINK YOU HAVE
GAMBLING PROBLEMS?
>> HOW MUCH MONEY HAVE YOU LOST?
>> 88,000.
>> HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS.
>> CAN THE TRUTH TEAM SAVE THEM?
>> WE HAD TO TAKE A DRUG TEST.
>> THE DRUG TEST RESULTS SHOW...
>> IT'S TIME TO FACE THE TRUTH.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Vivica: A DRUG USER, A
GAMBLER, AND A LIAR.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
NOT THE TERMS YOU WANT TO
DESCRIBE THE FATHER OF YOUR
CHILDREN.
THAT'S WHY OUR NEXT GUEST,
JAMIE, HAS HAD ENOUGH.
JAMIE SAYS SCOTT CAN'T BE
TRUSTED BECAUSE HE'S ADDICTED TO
DRUGS AND GAMBLING.
SHE SAYS HE GOES ON VENDORS AND
DISAPPEARS FOR DAYS.
JAMIE DOESN'T WANT HIM TO CLEAN
UP HIS ACT FOR HER -- SHE WANTS
THEM TO IMPROVE FOR THEIR THREE
KIDS.
SCOTT SAYS JAMIE IS OFF HER
ROCKER.
HE SAYS HE HAS CHANGED AND IS
STAYING AWAY FROM DRUGS AND WE
CAN SEE NOW.
HE
CLAIMS HE'S A BETTER PERSON NOW
AND WANTS JAMIE BACK.
SO, IS HE DEAD BEAT DAD, OR IS
SHE REALLY OFF HER ROCKER?
>> Vivica: HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BE DEALING WITH SCOTT'S
BEHAVIOR?
>> SCOTT AND I HAVE BEEN
INVOLVED FOR EIGHT YEARS ON AND
SOMETIMES OFF.
>> Vivica: SCOTT, IS IT TRUE
YOU'VE BEEN ON DRUG BENDERS FOR
DAYS AND DISAPPEARED?
>> UNFORTUNATELY, YES.
>> Vivica: HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN DOING THAT?
>> I'VE BEEN DOING IT FOR LIKE
FIVE YEARS BUT THERE HAVE BEEN A
LOT OF TIMES I'VE BEEN CLEAN AND
DOING WELL.
UNFORTUNATELY I RUIN THAT WHEN I
GO BACK ON TO BEING A BAD
PERSON.
>> Rosie: SCOTT, WHAT IF SOME
OF THE THINGS YOU PUT JAMIE
THROUGH?
>> I LATER ABOUT WHERE I'M AT.
>> Rosie: WHY?
>> IT'S HARD TO FACE THE TRUTH.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
[LAUGHTER]
WE ARE ALL HERE TO FACE THE
TRUTH.
>> Mary: JAMIE, WHEN HE USES
DRUGS, WHAT KIND DOES HE USE?
>> HE USES PCP.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Vivica: WHAT?
PCP?
SCOTT, DIDN'T THAT GO OUT IN THE
'80s?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Mary: PROBABLY BEFORE HE
WAS BORN!
>> Vivica: PCP?
>> WILL BE ARE FROM, WE CALL IT
WAVY.
SOMETIMES I WRITE OF THE
SURFBOARD.
>> Judy: THAT IS A MESSED UP
DRUG.
IT MAKES YOUR BRAIN SHUT OFF
CERTAIN COMMUNICATIONS
COMPLETELY.
PEOPLE HAVE SEIZURES, COMA HAS.
INCREASED RISK OF SUICIDE.
THERE'S A LOT OF REALLY TERRIBLE
THINGS THAT CAN COME WITH IT.
>> Rosie: DO KNOW WHEN HE'S ON
IT?
>> WHEN HE'S ON THAT HE IS SLOW
AND CREEPY.
>> Judy: SCOTT, I KNOW YOU'VE
SAID YOU TRIED TO KEEP SOME OF
THIS AWAY FROM YOUR FAMILY.
>> I'VE NEVER DONE IT WITH MY
KIDS, I'VE DONE ALL MY OWN TIME.
>> Judy: SO THAT MEANS YOU
MIGHT DISAPPEAR FOR A FEW DAYS
ON A DRUG --
>> Mary: WHAT DOES THAT MEAN
COME ON YOUR OWN TIME?
YOU HAVE YOUR OWN TIME, YOU HAVE
A FAMILY TO TAKE CARE OF.
[APPLAUSE]
"MY OWN TIME."
>> Judy: JAMIE, YOU THINK HE
HAS A GAMBLING PROBLEM?
>> I KNOW HE HAS CABLING
PROBLEM.
HE WILL TAKE HIS PAYCHECKS AND
GO STRAIGHT TO THE CASINO, AND
HE DISAPPEARS.
I HIT MY PHONE AND I START
GPSING HAS LOCATION.
>> Judy: AND YOU SEE HE'S AT
THE CASINO AND HASN'T MOVED,
BASICALLY.
>> I EITHER TRACK UP THE PHONE
OF A CAR.
I HAVE A TRACKER IN THE CAR AS
WELL.
>> Judy: YOU'VE BEEN TOGETHER
EIGHT YEARS ON AND OFF.
IS IT TRUE THESE PROBLEMS ONLY
STARTED FIVE YEARS AGO, RUBIES
ALWAYS PART OF THE PICTURE?
>> I DIDN'T KNOW HE HAD SUCH A
PROBLEM UNTIL AFTER OUR FIRST
DAUGHTER WAS BORN.
>> Rosie: WITH THE GAMBLING
PROBLEM, YOU GOT BANNED FROM A
CASINO.
WHY WAS THAT?
>> HE WAS ERRATIC AND HE WANTED
MORE AND MORE BECAUSE HE KEPT ON
LOSING HIS MONEY.
I DIDN'T WANT TO GIVE IT TO HIM.
HE GAVE THE MONEY TO ME, I SAID
"WE NEED TO PAY BILLS.
YOU ARE OBLIGATED TO PAY BILLS."
AND HE WANTED THE MONEY BACK
AFTER HE KEPT ON LOSING.
I SAID NO, AND HE TRIED TO
WRESTLE IT OUT OF MY HANDS.
>> Vivica: THE SCOTT, DO YOU
HAVE A GAMBLING ADDICTION?
>> I DEFINITELY DO.
>> Vivica: HOW LONG HAVE YOU
HAD A GAMBLING ADDICTION?
>> IT'S BEEN ON AND OFF FOR LIKE
TEN YEARS.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Vivica: TEN YEARS?
OVER THE TEN YEARS, HOW MUCH
MONEY WOULD YOU SAY YOU'VE LOST?
>> ONE TIME I WENT TO THE CASINO
AND THEY ASKED HOW MUCH MY LOSS
WAS FOR THE YEAR AND THEY SAID
$88,000.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
>> Judy:    B5 IF GAMBLING STARS
AGO, AND THE PCP WAS AFTER THAT,
ONE WAS THAT?
>> I FOUND OUT I LIKE USING IT
MORE THAN MARIJUANA SO I USE
THAT INSTEAD OF THE MARIJUANA.
>> Judy: WHEN DID YOU START
USING ALCOHOL?
>> WHEN I WAS LIKE 14.
>> Judy: AND MARIJUANA?
>> AROUND THE SAME TIME.
>> Judy: VERY EARLY TO BE
STARTING BOTH SUBSTANCES.
>> Mary: I JUST WANT TO KNOW
WHAT DRUGS SHE'S ON FOR STAYING
WITH HIM.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
>> Vivica: USE OF THE LOVE
DRUG?
LEVEL MAKE YOU DO SOME CRAZY
THINGS.
HE SAYS HE HAS LOST $88,000.
HOW MUCH WOULD YOU SAY HE'S
LOST?
>> THAT'S ONLY ONE YEAR, I
THINK, THAT HE'S TALKING ABOUT.
IT'S HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS.
>> ROSIE: WAS HE NOT PRESENT FOR
ONE OF THE PREGNANCIES, OR ALL
OF THEM?
>> HE WAS THERE FOR THE
PREGNANCY OF OUR FIRST DAUGHTER,
IT WAS AFTER SHE WAS BORN THAT
HE HAD AN EPISODE WHERE HE
DISAPPEARED AND HE WAS DOING
DRUGS AND GAMBLING.
HE WASN'T IN THE HOUSE.
>> Rosie: HOW OLD WAS YOUR
BABY AT THE TIME?
>> MAYBE LIKE SIX MONTHS.
>> Rosie: WOW.
>> Vivica: SCOTT, CAN I ASK
WHEN THE LAST TIME IS THAT
YOU'VE USED PCP?
>> I DID A STINT IN REHAB BACK
IN MAY AND I SUCCESSFULLY
COMPLETED THAT PROGRAM.
>> Mary: HOW LONG WAS THAT
PROGRAM?
>> I WAS IN THERE FOR TWO WEEKS
OF THE TIME.
>> Mary: TWO WEEKS?
THAT'S IT?
>> Judy: DO YOU THINK IT WAS
ENOUGH TO DO WITH YOUR ISSUES?
>> IT WAS A LIFE-CHANGING
EXPERIENCE.
JAMIE HAS BEEN OFF HER ROCKER
LATELY WITH THESE ACCUSATIONS
BECAUSE YOU THINK THAT BEEN
TURNED BACK INTO THE PERSON I
USED TO BE.
SHE GAVE ME ANOTHER CHANCE, I
TOOK THAT CHANCE AND RUN WITH IT
TO BE THE BEST PERSON -- DON'T
GET ME WRONG, I'VE GIVEN HER
SOME DOUBT BECAUSE THEY HAD A
RELAPSE OVER THE SUMMER.
SHE KNOWS ABOUT IT.
BUT SHE KEEPS ACCUSING ME EVERY
TIME I COME HOME.
IF SHE ALLOWS ME ON THE HOUSE --
>> Rosie: BUT YOU'VE CREATED
IT.
>> AND I HOLD, GOING UP TO THAT.
>> Vivica: I NEED YOU TO
UPHOLD THAT THAT FOR ME.
HIS SCOTT FACING HIS DEMONS, OR
IS HE STILL CAUGHT IN THE
ADDICTION?
>> HAS HE PAID ANY CHILD SUPPORT
SINCE YOU WERE SEPARATED?
>> GOT HIS COURT ORDERED PAY 20
$700 A WEEK FOR THREE CHILDREN.
How's your cough?
I'm good. I took 12-hour Mucinex
and sent it far away.
Hey buddy, have you seen a
nice woman with a cough?
Woahhh!
Mucinex DM releases fast and
lasts 12-hours, not 4.
Send coughs far away all day.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> IF YOU WOULD LIKE OUR TRUTH
TEAM TO HELP YOU SETTLE A
CONFLICT AND FIND A REAL
CONSTRUCTIVE RESOLUTION, CALL
323-843-3627.
OR EMAIL US AT
FaceTheTruthTV.COM.
IT'S TIME TO FACE THE TRUTH.
ARE YOU READY?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Vivica: JAMIE SAYS SCOTT IS
A DRUG USER, GAMBLER, AND CAN'T
BE TRUSTED.
SCOTT SAYS SHE'S OFF HER ROCKER.
JAMIE, HAS SCOTT PAID TO ANY
CHILD SUPPORT SINCE YOU TWO WERE
SEPARATED?
>> SCOTT IS COURT ORDERED TO PAY
$27 A WEEK FOR THREE CHILDREN.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
A >> Mary: THAT'S PROBABLY
BASED ON THE FACT THAT HE'S GOT
NO INCOME.
BECAUSE THAT'S PROBABLY THE
LOWEST OF THE SCALE WILL ALLOW.
>> Judy: WOW.
>> Rosie: YOU HAVE KIDS UP AT
HOME, YOU'VE SCREWED UP A WHOLE
BUNCH OF TIMES, YOU ARE GETTING
YOUR LIFE BACK TOGETHER, YOU ARE
DROPPING A JOB.
MEANWHILE, WHO WAS FEEDING HER
KIDS?
WYATT --
>> Mary: YOU ARE PAYING FOR
THESE KIDS, ROSIE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Judy: PART OF THE PROBLEM
AS HE WENT TO TWO WEEKS OF
TREATMENT.
JUST SO YOU KNOW, THE STANDARD
OF CARE IS 90 PLUS DAYS.
ESPECIALLY WITH SOMEBODY HAS
MULTIPLE ADDICTIONS LIKE YOU.
IT'S NOT SURPRISING TO ME THAT
YOU HAD A RELAPSE EARLIER THIS
YEAR.
JAMIE, TELL US ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED THERE.
>> I DIDN'T REALLY KNOW WHERE HE
WAS.
I HAD TO LOCATE HIM, AND I FOUND
THAT HE WASN'T IN AN AREA THAT
HE SHOULD BE IN.
HE CAME HOME.
HE WAS ACTING WEIRD.
THE PCP HAS A VERY DISTINCTIVE
SMELL.
I MADE HIM BREATHE SO I COULD
SNIFF IT, AND I WAS LIKE, "THAT
DOESN'T SMELL RIGHT."
AND I WENT IN LIKE A BLOODHOUND
IN HIS CAR AND SNIFFED IT OUT HE
FOUND IT.
>> Judy: WOW.
DID YOU SAY, SCOTT, THAT WAS THE
FIRST TIME YOU HAD RELAPSED?
OR WAS SUCH IS THE TIME YOU GOT
CAUGHT?
>> IT'S THE ONLY TIME PROBABLY
THAT HE GOT CAUGHT.
>> Judy: I KNOW THAT YOU SAID
YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN ON AND OFF.
WHAT'S THE CRITERIA WHEN YOU
DECIDE TO LET HIM BACK INTO YOUR
LIFE?
>> Rosie: WHY WOULD YOU LET
HIM BACK INTO YOUR LIFE?
>> Mary: WHY WOULD YOU PUT UP
WITH ALL OF THIS?
>> AT THIS POINT, WE HAVE THREE
KIDS TOGETHER.
[CRYING]
HE HAS MOMENTS WHERE SHE IS
WONDERFUL.
HE'S A GREAT FATHER.
I WANT THEM TO HAVE THEIR DAD
AROUND.
>> Judy: BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU?
ARE YOU GETTING SOME OF THAT
LOVE ALSO, WHEN HE IS SOBER?
>> WHEN HE'S CLEAN AND HE IS
SOBER, HE'S GREAT.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH HIM.
HE IS SUCCESSFUL, HE CAN HOLD A
JOB.
HE IS A GREAT PARTNER.
>> Judy: YEAH.
SO, JAMIE, CAN I JUST LET YOU
KNOW -- UNFORTUNATELY, SCOTT HAS
PUT YOU ON AN INTERMITTENT
REINFORCEMENT PLAN THE SAME WAY
THAT GAMBLING WORKS.
BECAUSE HE IS AROUND SOMETIMES,
AND YOU'RE NOT 100% SURE AND
CAN'T PREDICT WHEN THOSE GOOD
TIMES ARE.
>> RIGHT.
>> Judy: IN SOME WAYS, THAT'S
THE ADDICTIVE PROCESS.
THAT'S HOW YOU GET ADDICTED.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHEN THE PAYOFF
IS GOING TO BE.
SO NOW YOU ARE ADDICTED TO SCOT
SCOTT.
>> Rosie: JAMIE, DO YOU
BELIEVE HE'S CLEAN NOW?
>> I DON'T.
I JUST BELIEVE HE IS GONE MORE
THAN HE NEEDS TO BE.
I FEEL THAT WHEN I DO SEE HIM HE
IS ACTING PECULIAR, LIKE
SOMETHING IS UP.
I KNOW.
A BENEFIT FOR EIGHT YEARS, I
KNOW WHEN HE IS ON AND WHEN HE'S
OFF.
>> Judy: DO YOU FEEL LIKE HE
IS LYING?
>> HE LIES CONSTANTLY.
I FEEL LIKE EVERYTHING THAT
COMES OUT OF HIS MOUTH IS ALIVE.
>> Judy: OH, WOW.
SCOTT, HOW DOES THAT FEEL THE
HERO MUCH SHE DOESN'T TRUST YOU?
>> THAT'S THE MAIN ISSUE.
SHE HAS BEEN ABLE TO PUT THESE
THINGS BEHIND HER.
THE WINDSHIELD IS BIGGER THAN
THE REARVIEW MIRROR.
WHEN YOU WERE LOOKING OUT --
>> Rosie: BUT YOU'VE BEEN
DOING IT FOR THE LAST TEN YEARS.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT, BUT THERE
HAVE BEEN YEARS, A COUPLE YEARS,
WHERE I HAVEN'T DONE THAT.
>> Mary: AND THEN IT WENT INTO
A RELAPSE AND ANOTHER RELAPSE.
I HATE THAT WORD COME A RELAPSE.
"I RELAPSE, FORGIVE ME."
SHE SLITHERED WITH THE FEAR OF A
RELAPSE.
$27 FOR CHILD SUPPORT?
YOU COULD COLLECT CANS AND GET
RECYCLING AND GET $27.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH THE $27?
[APPLAUSE]
THESE KIDS HAVE GOT TO EAT.
>> Judy: SCOTT, HAVE YOU EVER
EXPERIENCED DEPRESSION OR
ANXIETY?
>> I WORK IN A STRESSFUL
ENVIRONMENT.
INSTEAD OF TAKING MY ANGER OUT
ON SOMEONE OR SOMETHING, I WOULD
GO USE.
I OWN IT UPON MYSELF TO ADMIT TO
MY PROBLEMS.
I HAVEN'T BEEN A GREAT PERSON,
AND I HAVE GIVEN HER EVERY
REASON TO NOT BE WITH ME.
BUT I HAVE ALSO AT TIMES GIVEN
HER A LOT OF REASONS TO BE WITH
ME.
>> Vivica: AND YOU CAN TALK
ABOUT IT, BUT BEING ABOUT IT IS
A WHOLE OTHER THING.
>> YOU GOT TO WALK IT LIKE YOU
TALK IT TALK AT.
>> Vivica: EXACTLY.
YOU'VE GOT TO PROVE TO HER THAT
YOU WANT IT.
SHE'S GOT TO SEE IT.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT, RIGHT?
>> RIGHT.
>> Vivica: BEFORE THE SHOW WE
HAD SCOTT TAKE A DRUG TEST.
WE WILL SEE IF HE'S TELLING THE
TRUTH AFTER THE BREAK.
[APPLAUSE]
>> COMING UP, IS SCOTT CLEAN AND
SOBER?
NOW YOU CAN VOTE ON THE TRUTH.
PLUS...
>> YOU HAVE NO PRESCRIPTION
DRUGS IN YOUR SYSTEM?
>> NO, MA'AM.
>> WELL, OUR
I know it's hard Maddie.
DRUGS IN YOUR SYSTEM?
>> NO, MABut I promise,
>> WEit's gonna get better.
♪ ♪
(mom giggles)
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50-85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
THE THREE WHAT?
THE THREE P'S?
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 54 AND I WAS
A SMOKER BUT QUIT.
ALEX, WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I'M 65, RETIRED,
AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
ALSO $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80
AND I'M ON A FIXED INCOME.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
THAT'S LESS THAN 35 CENTS A DAY.
YOU CANNOT BE TURNED DOWN
BECAUSE OF YOUR HEALTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
OPTIONS START AT $9.95 A MONTH,
PLUS, YOU GET A 30-DAY
MONEY BACK GUARANTEE.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Vivica: JAMIE SUSPECTS THE
FATHER OF HER CHILDREN IS BACK
TO USING DRUGS, BUT SCOTT SAYS
JAMIE IS OUT OF HER MIND AND HE
IS CLEAN AND SOBER.
AUDIENCE, WE WANT TO KNOW WHAT
YOU THINK.
IS SCOTT CLEAN AND SOBER?
PRESS YES OR NO ON YOUR TABLETS.
AND, AMERICA, YOU CAN VOTE AT
HOME TOO.
JUST GO TO OUR WEBSITE,
FaceTheTruthTV.com, TO LET US
KNOW WHAT YOU THINK.
♪ ♪
OKAY, THE RESULTS ARE IN.
57% OF YOU SAID, NO, SCOTT IS
NOT CLEAN AND SOBER.
JAMIE AND SCOTT, PLEASE COME
JOIN ME IN THE CIRCLE OF TRUTH.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
BEFORE THE SHOW, SCOTT, YOU TOOK
A DRUG TEST.
JUDGE MARY NOW HAS THOSE
RESULTS.
JUDGE MARY?
>> Mary: LET ME JUST ASK --
YOU HAVE NO PRESCRIPTION DRUGS
IN YOUR SYSTEM?
>> NO, MA'AM."
>> Mary: WELL, OUR DRUG TEST
RESULTS SHOW THAT YOU ARE
NEGATIVE ON EVERYTHING.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
GOOD JOB.
>> I'M SHOCKED.
>> Vivica: WHY ARE YOU
SHOCKED?
>> BECAUSE I JUST COULDN'T THINK
THAT HE WAS THAT CREEP YOU
NATURALLY.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Vivica: WELL, DAMN, JAMIE!
[LAUGHS]
WHAT ARE SOME OF THE BEHAVIORS
LIKE?
>> I DON'T KNOW, HE'S JUST
AWKWARD.
>> I'M AWKWARD BY NATURE!
I CAN RUB PEOPLE THE WRONG WAY
WITH THE WAY I AM.
I'M A LITTLE BIT DIFFERENT.
THAT'S JUST ME.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW...
WHEN I'M USING, I'M A WHOLE
OTHER PERSON, SOMEBODY THAT SHE
DEFINITELY SHOULD NOT BE WITH.
I WOULDN'T BLAME HER AT ALL FOR
NOT WANTING TO BE WITH THAT
PERSON.
I REALLY WOULDN'T.
>> Vivica: DO YOU REALLY LOVE
THIS WOMAN?
>> I LOVE HER TO DEATH.
SHE HAS CHANGED MY LIFE.
I KNOW THERE'VE BEEN TIMES WHERE
OF LET HER DOWN IN A VERY BIG
WAY, BUT SHE'S GIVEN ME THREE
BEAUTIFUL CHILDREN.
WE HAVE A STEPCHILD WE ALL LOVE.
I'M IN IT FOR THE LONG HAUL, AND
I WANT TO SHOW HER THAT I WILL
BE BY HER SIDE AND --
>> Vivica: READY TO GROW UP,
BASICALLY?
>> I NEED TO BE A MAN.
THE BOY NEEDS TO BECOME A MAN.
THAT'S WHAT I NEED TO DO.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Vivica: I LIKE HEARING
THAT.
WE WILL HEAR FROM THE TRUTH TEAM
NEXT.
>> COMING UP...
>> THIS BETTER BE YOUR DAY OF
RECKONING.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU USED?
>> PLUS...
>> MY LIFE, MY CHILDREN.
I HAVE LOVE FOR SCOTT AND I
WANTED TO DO RIGHT.
>> I WANT TO MAKE THIS DAY
SOMETHING TO REMEMBER.
SO, IF YOU DON'T MIND...
[AUDIENCE REACTS]EAS]
>> T
(Nora)
Before we start - how much is my
tax prep going to cost?
(Tax Guy)
I can't really say that until
the end.
(Lisa) [off-screen]
Wait, no.
H&R Block has upfront,
transparent pricing
so you know the price
before you begin.
(Nora)
So, it can work like that.
(Lisa)
Yup!
(Tax Guy)
Oh, so you want transparency.
Oh, um I could give you a
ballpark...
Ummm, hmmmm.
(Lisa)
That's not a price.
(Lisa VO) ♪
Know the price before you begin.
With new upfront transparent
pricing at H&R Block.
In-person or online.
Block has your back.
Who do you think
takes more pride
in how they craft
their orange juice?
e corporate executivesk
Coke and Pepsi,ide
the farmers ofcraft
orida's Natural?juice?
Only Florida's Natural
is always
made in Florida
by Florida farmers.
Great Taste.
Naturally.
Sometimes a cough gets in the
way of a good night's sleep.
That's when he needs Vicks
poRub.
Proven cough medicine.
With 8 hours of vapors, so he
can sleep.
Vicks VapoRub. Goodnight Coughs.
In terms of treating
sensitivity,
3 days is really fast.
Sensodyne Rapid Relief
is a game changer.
It's going to let the
dentist offer their
patient sensitivity relief
in 3 days.
Say over the course of a weekend
you're going to
start feeling
significant results.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Vivica: JAMIE AND SCOTT
HAVE HAD AN EIGHT YEAR DATING
HISTORY AND THREE KIDS.
JUDGE MARY?
>> Mary: THIS BETTER BE HER
DAY OF RECKONING.
MY QUESTION TO YOU -- BECAUSE
IT'S A VERY IMPORTANT DATE --
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU USED?
>> IT WAS AROUND AUGUST.
>> Mary: THAT'S BAD.
THAT'S A BAD ANSWER.
HE WANT TO KNOW WHY?
ANYBODY WHO HAS TURNED THEIR
LIFE AROUND IS THE EXACT DATE,
THE EXACT MOMENT.
THAT IS YOUR ANNIVERSARY DATE.
A VERY IMPORTANT DATE.
I DON'T GO SOMEWHERE AROUND
NOVEMBER.
NOVEMBER 20TH, 2002 I STOPPED
DRINKING.
THAT'S MY ANNIVERSARY.
IT'S TIME THAT YOU STARTED
ACTING LIKE A FATHER AND LIKE
THE MAN THAT SHE EXPECTS YOU TO
BE.
>> I AGREE, 100%.
>> Mary: LET THIS BE THE
ANNIVERSARY DATE.
>> I WILL.
>> Vivica: DR. JUDY?
>> Judy: YOU NEED TO MAKE A
COMMITMENT TO SOBRIETY.
THAT'S NOT ONLY TO SAY, "I'M
NEGATIVE TODAY."
WE CELEBRATE THAT SMALL VICTORY.
[APPLAUSE]
SO, SCOTT, I HOPE YOU CAN MAKE
THAT COMMITMENT TODAY AND SHOW
JAMIE WITH HER ACTIONS THAT YOU
ARE READY TO BE THE MAN SHE
DESERVES.
TRANSFORMATION TREATMENT CENTER
IS GOING TO HAVE ITS CLINICAL
TEAM DO A FULL ASSESSMENT OF
YOUR GAMBLING ADDICTION AND DRUG
USE, AND IF YOU ARE DETERMINED
TO BE A GOOD CANDIDATE, THEY
WILL COME UP WITH A CUP OR HEADS
OF TO HELP YOU KICK THIS ONCE
AND FOR ALL.
[APPLAUSE]
JAMIE AND SCOTT, SINCE YOU BOTH
NEED HELP GETTING YOUR CAREERS
BACK ON TRACK, CERTIFIED CAREER
COACH SHEENA LAURIE IS OFFERING
EACH OF YOU THREE CAREER
COACHING SESSIONS BACK IN YOUR
HOME STATE SO YOU CAN FIGURE
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO NEXT AND
REALLY PROVIDE FOR YOUR FAMILY
AND HAVE A CAREER YOU BOTH ARE
PROUD OF.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THANK YOU.
>> Vivica: ROSIE?
>> Rosie: GROW, TAKING CARE OF
YOUR KIDS, YOU'VE GOT TO REMEMBR
SOMETHING -- THAT LOVE
YOU'VE GIVEN SCOTT SO FREELY,
YOU OWE YOURSELF THAT LOVE.
YOU NEED TO TAKE CARE OF
YOURSELF.
IT'S PART OF SURVIVAL.
[APPLAUSE]
WE HAVE ARRANGED FOR A SPA DAY
AT HAVEN SPA NEW YORK FOR THEIR
"SPOIL ME" PACKAGE INCLUDING A
FACIAL MASSAGE AND A LOT MORE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Vivica: SEE?
I WAS TRYING TO MAKE IT THROUGH
THE DAY WITHOUT CRYING,
MISS JAMIE.
WHY ARE YOU GETTING SO
EMOTIONAL?
>> BECAUSE IT'S MY LIFE.
MY CHILDREN.
I HAVE LOVE FOR SCOTT, AND I
WANT HIM TO DO RIGHT.
>> VIVICA, I WANT TO MAKE THIS
DAY SOMETHING MORE TO REMEMBER.
SO, IF YOU DON'T MIND...
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
JAMIE, I KNOW I HAVEN'T BEEN THE
PERSON THAT YOU DESERVE.
NOW I WANT TO BE THE MAN THAT
YOU NEED.
I WANT TO PROVE TO YOU THAT I'M
GOING TO BE THAT FOREVER.
SO I WANT TO ASK YOU...
WILL YOU BE THE LOVE FOR THE
REST OF MY LIFE AND BECOME MY
WIFE?
I WANT TO PROVE TO YOU THAT I'M
GOING TO BE RIGHT BY YOU GUYS.
>> YES!
>> Vivica: YES!
[APPLAUSE]
SHE SAID YES!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THAT IS OUR GOAL HERE AT
"FACE THE TRUTH," FOR PEOPLE TO
FACE THE TRUTH.
KNOW THAT WE WANT YOU GUYS TO
LIVE YOUR BEST LIVES.
IT SETS WITH YOU.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> Vivica: YOU ARE GOING TO BE
THE MAN OF HIS FAMILY.
>> I WANT TO TAKE THE STEPS TO
DO THAT.
>> Vivica: YOU'VE GOT TO BUILD
HER TRUST.
PLEASE TAKE THE COUNSELING.
PLEASE GIVE HELP.
>> I WILL.
>> Vivica: WE WHITE GUYS TO
LIVE YOUR BEST LIVES
, OKAY?
[SIGH]
JAMIE AND SCOTT, THANK YOU FOR
HAVING THE COURAGE TO FACE THE
TRUTH.
KNOW THAT WE WISH YOU THE
ABSOLUTE BEST.
OKAY?
>> THINK FOR HAVING US.
[APPLAUSE]
HUGHES
WAS COMING UP IN OUR NEXT HALF
HOUR.
>> DO YOU BLAME WHAT HAPPENED TO
YOU ON YOUR HUSBAND?
>> I DO.
IS HE IS INNOCENT AS HE SAYS?
>> DOES REMIND YOU THAT FIRST
TIME THIS ALSO DO?
>> FIND OUT AS THEY --
>> DO YOU THINK HE MIGHT BE
SEEING OTHER WOMEN?
>> AFTER THAT TEXT MESSAGE...
>> IT'S TIME TO FACE THE TRUTH.
>> Vivica: SEE YOU NEXT TIME.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> THE FOLLOWING PROGRAM
CONTAINS MATURE SUBJECT MATTER.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.