A NEW STEAK AND BOURBON ICE
CREAM.■a■aóaóa
THESE GUYS ARE GOING TO TRY.
>> THE BIGGEST SCOOP OF MY
LIFE, IT IS Hp
>> DOES IT TASTE LIKE MEAT?
>> HE REALLY TAKE THE BOURBON,
BOURBON IS GOOD.
>> HARD SEASONING, YOU YC
■CMEAT?
>> A LITTLE BACON ON TOP AS
WE
THANKS FOR THIS MARVELOUS
T-SHIRT, A GREAT GIFT.■)p@■7@@
COME ON.■4■■■■',',■8■8■8o>, IT
LOT OF FUN.
>> OH MY GOD!
OH MY GOD!
>> CALIFORNIA BRACING WITH A
SECOND EARTHQUAKE STRIKING,
FOUNDATIONS OF ROADS CRACKING,
AND NOW THE FEAR ANOTHER ONE
COULD BE COMING AS CALIFORNIA
GOVERNOR GAVIN NEWSOM DECLARES
A STATE OF EMERGENCY IN SAN
BERNARDINO COUNTY.
WELCOME, HAPPY WEEKEND, I AM
NEO AND YOU ARE LOOKING
AT LOS ANGELES INTERNATIONAL
AIRPORT WHERE ALL IS CALM AFTER
■
RIDGECREST CALIFORNIA
WHERE THE FIRST EPICENTER, THAT
IS WHERE YOU'LL FIND JEFF IN
THE MIDDLE OF ALL.
HOW ARE THINGS THERE NOW?
>> Reporter: THERE'S A GENERAL
FEELING OF UNEASINESS, TWO
DAYS, TWO BIG MASSIVE
EARTHQUAKES NEAR THIS TOWN IN
CALIFORNIA AND THIS LATEST ONE,
SEVERAL AFTERSHOCKS IN THE LAST
FEW MINUTES OR SO WHEN WE WERE
WAITING TO SPEAK WITH YOU, WE
FELT SEVERAL OF THEM AT CITY
HALL AND THAT UNEASINESS IS
LEADING MANY PEOPLE NOT WANTING
TO LEAP -- SLEEP INSIDE THEIR
HOUSE LASTLY.
WE CAUGHT UP WITH THE SHERIFF'S
DEPUTY GOING STREET TO STREET
TO MAKE SURE PEOPLE WERE OKAY.
HE SAW A LOT OF PEOPLE LIVING
OUTSIDE OR COMING HERE TO CITY
HALL WHERE THERE IS A SHELTER
SET UP.
MAYBE WE COULD PULL UP THE
ACTUAL SOUND ON THIS.
THIS IS THE MOMENT WE WERE AT A
RESTAURANT, STARTED TO FEEL THE
RUMBLING, THE VIOLENT SHAKING
AND THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED AFTER
THAT.
TAKE A LISTEN. YOU COULD REALLC
IN PEOPLE'S VOICES.
THIS WAS A RESTAURANT RIGHT
HERE IN RIDGECREST AND T
WAS A SLIGHT AFTERSHOCK BEFORE
THIS AND EVERY ONE, THEY HAVE
BEEN THROUGH A FEW IN THE LAST
DAY BUT  THE 7.1
THE WHOLE BUILDING WAS SHAKING,
DISHES CRASHING ON THE GROUND
AND YOU COULD SEE PEOPLE IN
DISBELIEF, SOME HITTING THE
GROUND IN TEARS AND SHORTLY
AFTER WALKING OUT OF THIS
RESTAURANT WE LOOKED INTO THE
DISTANCE AND WE SEE A HUGE
PLUME OF SMOKE, WE GET CLOSER
AND REALIZE THIS HOUSE IS ON
FIRE AND THIS IS AT LEAST ONE
HOUSE THAT WAS SET ON FIRE, A
LOT OF THESE FRTED
BECAUSE OF RUPTURED GAS LINES.
WE ARE ONLY HEARING OF SOME
MINOR INJURIES, AND THINGS
FALLING ON PEOPLE, REPORTS OF
ANY DEPTH BUT THE GOVERNOR HAS
DECLARED A STATE OF EMERGENCY,
HAS REQUESTED A PRESIDENTIAL
DECLARATION, HELP FROM THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT.
SO FAR THE PRESIDENT HASN'T
TWEETED ABOUT WHAT HAS HAPPENED
IN CALIFORNIA.
>> CALIFORNIA GOVERNOR GAVIN
NEWSOM HAS DECLARED A STATE OF
EMERGENCY FOR AT LEAST SAN
BERNARDINO COUNTY AND BRACING
FOR MORE.
THAT HAS EVERYONE ON
TENTERHOOKS.
WHAT KIND OF MORE DOES THAT
MEAN?
HOW MUCH MORE?
ON THE PHONE WITH US IS PUBLIC
INFORMATION OFFICER FROM THE
GOVERNOR'S OFFICE AND EMERGENCY
SERVICE, THANK YOU FOR TAKING
THE TIME.
HOW ARE THINGS LOOKING?
>> WE HAVE BEEN WORKING
OVERNIGHT SINCE THE SECOND
EARTHQUAKE HAPPENED YESTERDAY
EVENING.
THE SECOND EARTHQUAKE HAPPENED
RIGHT BEFORE SUNSET, DARKNESS
PREVENTED US FROM DOING A LOT.
WE JUST HAD SUNRISE IN
CALIFORNIA IN THE LAST HOUR SO
IT IS CRUCIAL FOR US GETTING
INTO RIDGECREST AND AFFECTED
AREAS TO SEE WHAT DAMAGE WE ARE
TALKING AB■■D THERE
ARE SOME INJURIES BUT WE DON'T
KNOW HOW MUCH ANARD
INSIDE THEIR HOMES.NT TO GO
WE NEE WHAT NEEDS THEY
.
"CAVUTO" WE HAVE NOT HEARD
REPORTS OF SIGNIFICANT
INJURIES.
>> WE ARE HAVING BRIEFINGS ALL
NIGHT, CREWS AROUND THE
OPERATIONS CENTER.
WE HAVE SERIOUS INJURIES, THERE
ARE SOME BUT HOW MUCH, HOW
SERIOUS THE INJURIES THEY ARE,
HOSPITALS HAVE BEEN EVACUATED
IN SOME OF THE POWER LINES AND
GAS LINES HAVE BEEN BROKEN SO
WE NEED TO GET IN AND FIND OUT
WHAT WE ARE DEALING WITH.
>> THESE AFTERSHOCKS ARE MORE
SIGNIFICANT THAN THE MENT
BY A FACTOR OF 10 TIMES AND I'M
WONDERING HOW UNUSUAL IS THAT
FOR IANS WHO ARE ALWAYSACED FO
THIS KIND OF STUFF?
■ WILL DEFER TO THE
GEOLOGISTS WE HAVE BEEN TALKING
TO FOR THE PAST 48 HOURS.
NOT THAT UNCOMMON AND WHAT WE
ARE SEEING IS THE INITIAL
EARTHQUAKE WE SAW WAS NOT
CONSIDERED A MAIN EARTHQUAKE,
THE BIGGER THE EARTHQUAKE, THAT
BECOMES THE MAIN ONE.
NOW IS 7.1.
IT HAPPENED YESTERDAY EVENING,
THAT WAS THE MAIN EARTHQUAKE
AND THE ONE ON THE FOURTH OF
JULY IS BEING CALLED A 4 SHOCK.
NOT THAT UNCOMMON IF YOU TALK
TO THE GEOLOGISTS.
NEIL: WE GET ANECDOTAL REPORTS,
A PEOPLE AFRAID TO SLEEP IN
THEIR HOME SO THEY ARE IN THEIR
DRIVEWAY OR SLEEPING OUTSIDE,
THEY ARE THAT ANXIOUS.
HOW WIDESPREAD IS THAT?
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN IN RIDGECREST
BUT I DON'T BLAME THEM.
IT HAS BEEN 48 HOURS IN THE
SHAKING HAS BEEN VERY VIOLENT
AT TIMES AND PEOPLE WANT TO BE
OUTSIDE TO FEEL A LITTLE SAFER
AND THE PROBLEM IS WHAT WE HAVE
EARTHQUAKES IS CAN'T PREDICT
WHEN THE NEXT ONE WILL HAPPEN.
YOU CAN TRY TO GIVE ADVANCED
WARNING BUT EVEN SECONDS IS A
GOOD MORNING.
IF THERE'S A TRAIN RUNNING
THROUGH THE AREA WE STOP
ELEVATORS BUTT HAVE A
SYSTEM THAT CAN PREDICT FROM
MINUTES AWAY WHEN SOMETHING
WILL HAPPEN.
NEIL: YOU'VE HAD LITTLE IF ANY
SLEEP SO WE APPRECIATE YOU
UPDATING US.
THE GOVERNOR'S OFFICE OF
EMERGENCY SERVICES, THE
PRESIDENT WAS BRIEFED ON THIS.
THIS MORNING, UPDATES ON THAT
7.1 MAGNITUDE EARTHQUAKE.
ALLISON BARBER IS WITH THE
PRESIDENT, WHERE THE
COMMANDER-IN-CHIEF IS SPENDING
THE WEEKEND.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS DONALD
TRUMP WAS BRIEFED ON THE LATEST
EARTHQUAKE IN CALIFORNIA
OVERNIGHT, AROUND 1:00 AM THE
WHITE HOUSE SAID THEY HAD TEAMS
CLOSELY MONITORING THE
SITUATION IN CALIFORNIA SO THEY
WOULD BE PROVIDING UPDATES TO
THE PRESIDENT THROUGHOUT THE
NIGHT, DONALD TRUMP IS IN NEW
JERSEY STAYING AT A GOLF CLUB
IN THAT MINSTER AND AS OF THIS
MORNING TWEETING ABOUT
IMMIGRATION, JOE BIDEN AND THE
ECONOMY.
THE PERMIT OF LABOR SAYS US
ECONOMY ADDED 20,000 JOBS IN
JUNE, THAT IS UP FROM 72,000 IN
MAY.
>> OUR COUNTRY CONTINUES TO DO
REALLY WELL, REALLY REALLY
WELL.
WE ARE VERY HAPPY ABOUT IT.
WE ARE GOING TO BE BREAKING
RECORDS.
TO LOWER INTEREST RATES IT
WOULD BE LIKE A ROCKETSHIP.
>> Reporter: DONALD TRUMP
CONTINUES CRITIQUES OF THE
FEDERAL RESERVE ON TWITTER
WRITING OTHER COUNTRIES AROUND
THE WORLD ARE DOING ANYTHING
POSSIBLE TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF
THE UNITED STATES KNOWING OUR
FEDERAL RESERVE DOES NOT HAVE A
CLUE.
AGGRESSIVELY CRITICIZED D
REPEATEDLY GONE AFTER THE FED
AND THE CHAIRMAN.
HE CRITICIZED THE FED FOR
RAISING RATES, NOT DOING ENOUGH
TO HELP THE US ECONOMY, JAY
POWELL HAS EMPHASIZED THE FED
IS INDEPENDENT AND WHEN ASKED
ABOUT DONALD TRUMP, REPORTED
THE FED WOULD NEVER TAKE
POLITICAL CONSIDERATION INTO
ACCOUNT OR DISCUSS THEM AS PART
OF THEIR WORK.
HE SAID THEIR PRIORITY WAS
WORKING FOR THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE.
>> WITH THE PRESIDENT IN NEW
JERSEY.
WITH A STRONG JOBS REPORT IT IS
TOUGH TO MAKE THE CASE THAT THE
ECONOMY IS JUST TANKING.
WHAT DO DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES
DO?
That Karl brought his
karaoke machine?
♪ Ain't nothing but
a heartache... ♪
No, I can't believe how easy
it was to save hundreds of
dollars on my car
insurance with GEICO.
♪ I never wanna
hear you say... ♪
No, Kevin...
no, Kevin!
Believe it!
GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
or more on car insurance.
GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
My mom washes the dishes...
...before she puts them in the
dishwasher.
So what does the dishwasher do?
Cascade Platinum does the work
for you,
prewashing and removing
stuck-on foods,
the first time.
Wow, that's clean!
Cascade Platinum.
When I book at Hilton.com
I get to select my room
from the floor plan...
Free Wi-Fi...
...and the Price
MSo with Hilton.
tho catch.
Yeah the only catch
is I'm never leaving.
No I'm serious,
I live here now.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
>> OUR ECONOMY MUCH BETTER THAN
IT HAS EVER BEEN.
FROM ELECTION DAY, 50% INCREASE
AND WE PAID TRILLIONS OF
DOLLARS.
NEIL: A 50% INCREASE, THE DOW
JONES INDUSTRIAL SURGING SINCE
HE WAS FIRST ELECTED, THE
PRESIDENT SAYING HE IS A BIG
REASON FOR THAT AND OPTIMISM
AHEAD OF HIS INAUGURATION AND
WHAT HE HAS DONE SINCE HAVE
MADE THE CHANGES AND BOOMING
JOBS REPORT FEW PEOPLE SAW
COMING.
2020 DEMOCRATS PORTRAYING AN
ECONOMY NOT NEARLY AS ROBUST AS
THE NUMBERS INDICATE, LAUREN
LEADER IT IS WITH US, JOSEPH
PINION AND HOST OF FOX NATION,
BEGIN WITH WHAT THE PRESIDENT
IS SAYING, DENYING THE NUMBERS,
CREDIT FOR THOSE NUMBERS.
>> THAT IS THE SECOND PART A
LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH.
THE ECONOMY IS DOING VERY WELL,
THAT IS OBJECTIVELY TRUE AND
WELL THE ECONOMY IS DOING SO IF
ANY OTHER PRESIDENT IT WOULD BE
AND IT HAS BEEN.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH IT WILL
AFFECT COMMAND AT THE SAME
TIME, POLLS HAVEN'T ALWAYS
ACCURATELY REPRESENTED HOW MUCH
SUPPORT THE PRESIDENT HAS IF
YOU LOOK AT 2016.
IT IS HARD TO SAY BUT IT WILL
BE HARD FOR THE DEMOCRATS
BECAUSE THEY CAN'T SAY THE
ECONOMY IS A DISASTER, HARD TO
ARGUE AGAINST SOMETHING THAT IS
DOING SO WELL.
NEIL: YOU CAN'T SAY THE ECONOMY
--
>> GALLUP POLL TAKEN A COUPLE
WEEKS AGO COMPARED TO A YEAR
AGO WHICH IS INDEPENDENT OF
POLITICAL QUESTIONS BUT HOW DO
YOU VIEW THE ECONOMY.
46% OF AMERICANS THINK THE
ECONOMY IS POOR OR VERY BAD AND
THAT IS THE SAME NUMBER IT WAS
A YEAR AGO.
NEIL: HOW WAS UNDER BARACK
OBAMA?
>> I DIDN'T LOOK AT EVERY
SINGLE YEAR.
IT WAS A DIFFERENT TIME BECAUSE
WE WERE STILL COMING OUT OF
RECESSION.
THE POINT IS THE PRESIDENT, IT
SHOULD LOOK LIKE A BETTER
PICTURE.
THE IMPACT OF THE TARIFFS ON
FARMERS IN THE MIDWEST, ONGOING
TRADE GROWTH IS BEGINNING TO
CHANGE, STARTING TO RISE
SLIGHTLY.
VAST MAJORITY OF AMERICANS
COULDN'T MANAGE A $200
UNEXPECTED MEDICAL --
NEIL: THAT HAS BEEN THE CASE
ARE DEMOCRAT AND REPUBLICAN
PRESIDENTS.
>> DEMOCRATS WILL SAY OF THE
ECONOMY SO GOOD WHY AREN'T WE
INVESTING IN THE WORKING CLASS
TO RDEBT, TALK ABOUT
TRILLIONS --
NEIL: LIKE ME GIVING DIETARY
ADVICE.
>> THE DEBT HAS EXPLODED UNDER
THIS ADMINISTRATION.
NEIL: UNDER THE PRIOR ONE.
ONE OF THE THINGS THE PRESIDENT
HASN'T BEEN ABLE TO TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF, THE POINTS THAT
WERE RAISED, THERE WERE 1
MILLION MORE AFRICAN-AMERICANS
EMPLOYED THAN WHEN BARACK OBAM■
LEFT OFFICE.
WITH THOSE GROUPS HE IS STILL
UNDERWATER.
WHY IS THAT?
>> MESSAGING ACROSS THE BOARD,
THEY ARE BETTER SERVED NOT
TALKING ABOUT HISPANIC
IMPLEMENT A BLACK UNEMPLOYMENT
BUT WE HAVE A PROBLEM WITH
POVERTY.
HAVING SAID THAT IF DEMOCRATS
TELL YOU PEOPLE ING TWO
WITH THREE JOBS THEY HAVE BEEN
THIS WHOLE TIME.
THE DIFFERENCES THOSE TWO OR
THREE JOBS ARE PAYING MORE
UNDER MY ADMINISTRATION.
NEIL: PEOPLE WORKING TWO OR
MORE JOBS, A HARD NUMBER
NEVERTHELESS BUT EVERYBODY IS
WORKING.
>> WAGE GROWTH IS TAKING UP AS
JOB GROWTH IS TICKING UP.
WAGE GROWTH FOR
AFRICAN-AMERICANS AND HISPANICS
HAS NO
NEIL: IT HAS BEENAE■E■E■E■E■E■E
TO 3%.
>> DOUBLE THAT THROUGH WHITE
AMERICA.
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS
TARGETING DEMOCRATS CLOSER TO
3%, NOT NARROWING THE GAP BUT
IT IS BEGINNING TO.
WHAT I'M LOOKING AT IS WHETHER
THE ARGUMENTS DEMOCR
RAISING WILL COME BACK TO BITE
THEM BECAUSE MOST PEOPLE LOOK
AT THIS, I CAN DEAL WITH THIS.
>> IT WILL BE TOUGH, FOCUSING
ON OTHER THINGS LIKE
HEALTHCARE.
THAT THE GOOD THING TO FOCUS ON
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY REPUBLICANS
HAD A CHANCE TO FIX THAT AND
THAT GOT MESSED UP.
>> I THINK HE STOMPS ON HIS OWN
-- STOP SAYING AND GET AWAY.
>> HE DISTRACTS FROM THE
MESSAGE OF THE ECONOMY.
HE TALKS ABOUT IT BUT THEN HE
WILL TWEET SOMETHING ALL THE
WAY OUT THERE OR GO AFTER
SOMEBODY, CALL SOMEONE A LOSER
AND PEOPLE FOCUS ON THOSE
THINGS MORE THAN THE ECONOMY.
I AM A LOSER, I ALREADY KNOW
I'M A LOSER, WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO?
NEIL: WHEN I LOOK AT THE
DATA
THAT COMES IN, BIG STATES LIKE
PENNSYLVANIA, MICHIGAN AND
INDIANA WE ARE TALKING WAGES
GROWING FASTER THAN THE REST OF
THE NATION YET TO YOUR POINT HE
IS TRAILING BY DOUBLE DIGITS SO
-- NOT IN INDIANA.
WHOLE PICTURE.
AT THE SAME TIME WE HAVE IN
COMMON TO GROWTH WHICH WE DON'T
DENY IS REAL AND THE GROWTH IN
JOBS YOU HAVE THIS EXPLOSION,
THE ACCESS TO THE AMERICAN
DREAM GOT MORE EXPENSIVE,
WEIGHING DOWN MORE FAMILIES,
NOT JUST THE KIDS WHO WERE TOLD
THE GRANDPARENTS WHO WERE
SADDLED WITH DEBT, THE RISING
COST OF HEALTHCARE AND HOUSING
THEY TALKED ABOUT, COST OF
LIVING IN EVERY METROPOLITAN
AREA.
>> AND BENEFITS ILLEGALS.
IS THAT ENOUGH TO TURN THE
TIDE?
>> CHALLENGES OF WORKING-CLASS
AND MIDDLE-CLASS AMERICANS, AND
BENEFITING FROM THE STOCK
MARKET EXCEPT MAYBE A 401(K).
AND ANOTHER 46%.
THE POINT IS --
NEIL: WHAT ABOUT THE NUMBERS ON
MINORITY GAINS?
>> ALL THE POLLS THAT ASK
WORKING-CLASS AMERICANS HOW
THEY FEEL, DO THEY FEEL THEY
ARE BENEFITING FROM THIS
ECONOMY THE ANSWER IS NO THEY
DO NOT.
NEIL: HIGH MARKS IN THE ECONOMY
BUT NOT FOR HIM HIMSELF.
>> DEMOCRATS HAVE AN
OPPORTUNITY TO SAY I HAVE A
SOLUTION FOR THAT.
NEIL: THE ECONOMY --
>> THE REALITY, NOT EVERYONE
INVESTING IN THE STOCK MARKET.
IT WILL BE DIFFICULT.
NEIL: BENEFITING FROM THE
HIGHER MARKET OR PENSION FUNDS
THAT ARE DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY
INVESTED.
>> MUCH CONFIDENCE IS AN
INDICATOR ON -- IF YOU TAKE A
STEP BACK.
NEIL: WE ARE THINKING OF PEOPLE
FOR WHOM THE MARKET BOOM --
>> I RECOGNIZE PEOPLE SAY I AM
NOT INCLUDED IN THIS GROUP.
DIFFICULT FOR DEMOCRATS TO
STAND UP AND SAY YOUR 401(K)
GOING UP IS YOUR IMAGINATION.
NEIL: THE FACT THAT ON THESE ■i
WEDGE ISSUES AND WHAT YOU'RE
DOING ON ILLEGAL IMMIGRANTS AND
HEALTHCARE FOR ALL WILL
REGISTER.
>> IT IS A BIGGER PICTURE THAN
THE STOCK MARKET.■■@■@■
NEIL: THINGS THAT WILL LEAK OUT
SUPPORT.
>> DEMOCRATS HAVE A BIG STAGE
FOR THE NEXT 6 MONTHS, AND
POLICY SOLUTIONS, THEY WILL OWN
THAT AND THE PRESIDENT --
NEIL: OUT OF STEP WITH
DEMOCRATIC VOTERS, HEALTH
BENEFITS TO ILLEGALS.
>> THE BUT HE DOESN'T HAVE A
JOB YESTERDAY AND SOMEBODY WHO
HAS A JOB TOMORROW NOT BEING
ABLE TO CONVINCE THEM THEIR
LIFE IS WORSE OFF.
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO TALK ABOUT
THE VISCERAL IMPACT DONALD
TRUMP'S WORDS HAVE ON EVERYDAY
LIFE.
WHEN YOU SHOW UP IN NOVEMBER,
AND --
>> SOMETHING WE HAVE NEVER
SEEN, AND THE FEDERAL RESERVE
TO CUT INTEREST RATES.
IS THERE SOMETHING I AM
MISSING?
(ding)
Hey, who are you?
Oh, hey Jeff, I'm a car thief...
What?!
I'm here to
steal your car because,
well, that's my job.
What?
What??
WHAT?!
(laughing)
What??
WHAT?!
What?!
[crash]
WHAT?!
Haha, it happens.
And if you've got
cut-rate car insurance,
paying for this could
feel like getting robbed twice.
So get Allstate...
and be better
■ from Mayhem...
ñ[           me.
This is the couple who
wanted to get away
who used Expedia to book
the vacation rental
which led to the discovery
that sometimes
can lift you right up.
Expedia.
Everything you need to go.
■p          Expedia.
■■■■■■■
Coach! It's kinda hard to see
the ball.
I've been there.
I had a TV service with hardly
any sports in 4K.
Couldn't see any of the quality
details.
I switched to DIRECTV, now I get
the most live sports in 4K.
So how does that help me?
It really doesn't.
I don't know why I told you
that. Go get 'em sport!
Live sports that aren't in 4K
are just kinda TV.
Don't just kinda TV. DIRECTV
Don't have 4K? Call
1.855.WATCH.4K and ask for it
today.
>> GETTING OUR FIRST IMAGES,
AND THE SUN BEGINS TO RISE.
THESE ARE FROM KT TV, 7.1
MAGNITUDE EARTHQUAKE, MAKING IT
HIGHER BY A FACTOR TEN TIMES
THAN IT WAS 24 HOURS AGO, NO
REPORTS OF SERIOUS INJURY OR
WORSE SO FAR.
THERE IS THAT.
WE WILL KEEP YOU POSTED ON
AFTERSHOCKS■bc■bcbbcbbcbbcbbcb#
AND LET'S GET THE VIEW FROM
WEALTH MANAGEMENT AND AARON
GIBBS.
AND OUR VERY OWN FOXBUSINESS
NETWORK'S DEIRDRE BOLTON.
THAT WAS THE BATTLE BACK AND
FORTH YESTERDAY.
IT IS STRONG AND WE LIKE THAT.
GOOD NEWS IS GOOD NEWS BUT THAT
IS WHEN IT MEANS THE FEDERAL
RESERVE --
HARRIS: IF WE LOOK AT WHAT
TRADERS ARE ANTICIPATING, MOST
PEOPLE ARE LOSING THIS IN JULY.
THE IDEA OF A 50 BASIS POINT
CUT SEEMS TO NOT BE A REAL
POSSIBILITY.
AND TO YOUR POINT DO WE NEED IT
ALL OR DO WE NEED IT NOW?
THE MARKET CLEARLY PRICING IT
IN.
AND THE LAST PIECE OF DATA THE
FED WAS GETTING LAST FRIDAY,
THERE WERE A FEW THINGS YOU
COULD NOT BE THRILLED WITH.
THE WAGE GROWTH STARTED TO
DROP.
NEIL: 1%.
>> NOT AS STRONG.
THERE IS A CONCERN ABOUT TRADE
WAR, SLOWLY MOVING FORWARD.
THE LAST TIME THEY TALKED THE
BIG ISSUE WAS CONCERN, THE
GLOBAL ECONOMIC SLOWDOWN.EEEEEE
THE US IS GOOD, AT THE END OF
JULY.
>> THE ENVIRONMENT WE HAVE, THE
STRONG ECONOMY NOT AS STRONG AS
WE HAD BUT DON'T HAVE A LOT OF
ARROWS IN YOUR QUIVER.
DO YOU WAIT TO DO TIME IN AN
ENVIRONMENT AS GOOD AS THIS?
>> LIKE THAT MOVIE THE FAST AND
FURIOUS WHEN YOU THE NITROUS
TOO EARLY?
NEIL: THE EXACT SAME THING.
>> IT IS PSYCHOLOGICAL.
ON PURE INFLATION TERMS WE
COULD HAVE LOWER INTEREST
RATES.
GOOD TO HAVE THE INTEREST RATE
CURVE BE UPWARDS.
PEOPLE ARE CONCERNED WITH THAT.
IF THEY DO THAT, 1% OR 1.5 --
>> A LITTLE MORE.
IF THEY DO THAT, WAIT A SECOND,
WE ARE ALREADY RECYCLING THE
MONEY, WE ARE DOWN TO 1%.
WE ARE INCREASING SPENDING AND
A LITTLE PANIC AND IF THE FED
WANTS TO SHOW OFF YOU DON'T
HAVE THAT MANY LEFT AT THIS
POINT.
NEIL: THE TREASURY NOTES AND
BONDS --
>> THEY COULD GET OUT OF IT AND
TRYING TO SLOWLY WHAT THE
INTEREST PAYMENTS -- MORE
LONG-TERM DEBT WHICH IS THE
REASON INTEREST RATES FELL SO
MUCH DESPITE THE ECONOMY
SLOWING WHICH GETS THE WHOLE
THING, WHAT IS GOING ON IS THE
MARKET -- IN THE SHORT RUN
THERE WAS A BIG BET THAT THE
ECONOMY IS WEAKENING, GETTING
THE FED TO LOWER RATES AND IT
IS NOT THAT WEEK SO WE GET A
BIG BOOST AND THAT STORY
CHANGED.
NEIL: THEY SAY A GREAT REPORT
WILL BE REPORTED FAVORABLY AND
A BAD REPORT, THAT SETS YOU UP.
>> GOOD NEWS IS BAD NEWS, BAD
NEWS IS GOOD NEWS BUT WHEN YOU
TALK ABOUT THE TOOL I THINK THE
FED DECIDED THAT BY CUTTING
RATES, NOT CUTTING RATES, THE
QE WAS DIFFICULT AND THERE WAS
A BIT OF HOCUS-POCUS.
NEIL: THE PRESIDENT WAS A
CRITIC AND DO THAT FOR ME AND
REALLY AWESOME.
>> IT COULD BE ADDED BACK IN
BUT THE TIGHTENING, THEY LET IT
GET SO OUT OF HAND FOR SO LONG.
JUST SMALL QUARTER POINT RATE
CUTS.
THE IDEA OF A CUT FOR THIS WAS
A LITTLE AGGRESSIVE.
THE EXPECTATIONS ARE MORE
RATIONAL.
>> TALKING ABOUT DEFLATIONARY
WORRIES, TO YOUR POINT THERE
WERE A LOT OF PEOPLE, THERE
WERE DEFINITE ARGUMENTS BEING
MADE IN THE WASHINGTON POST,
THE ECONOMY, BLOOMBERG
BUSINESSWEEK, NO ONE IS SAYING
THIS IS HAPPENING BUT SHOULD
THIS BE NOW WHAT WE ARE WORRIED
ABOUT?
NEIL: I ALWAYS SAY WE HAVEN'T
GOT THE IMPACT OF TARIFFS
BECAUSE A LOT OF THEM HAVEN'T
REACHED CONSUMERS YET.
OBVIOUSLY EVENTUALLY THAT WILL
HAPPEN.
IF THEY GET A TRADE DEAL ALL
BETS ARE OFF.
THE FUNNY THING IS IF WE LOWER
INTEREST RATES, THE WEAKENED
DOLLAR HAS THE EFFECT OF THE
TARIFF AND COUNTRY SEE 5% OR
10% INCREASE IN THE PRESIDENT
WAS TALKING ABOUT HAVING RATES
TOO HIGH, THE DOLLAR IS TOO
STRONG.
NEIL: HE WOULD IMPROVE --
>> OTHER EXPORTERS, GERMANY IS
HAPPY WITH OUR 2% AND THEY HAVE
--
>> GERMANY, ACTUALLY YOU ARE
PAYING FOR THE PRIVILEGE TO
LEND YOUR MONEY TO THE
GOVERNMENT.
THEY HAVE NEGATIVE RATES.
NEIL: ARE WE GOING THERE?
>> I DON'T SEE IS GOING TO
NEGATIVE RATES.
WE ARE IN A HEALTHIER
ENVIRONMENT.
NEIL: ARE WE AT THIS STAGE?
>> I AM
BULLISH BUT I AM
CAUTIOUSLY OPTIMISTIC.
>> WE WOULD PROBABLY BE 1%.
THE ECONOMY, STRONGER INFLATION
BUT WE BORROW MUCH MORE.
THE ACTUAL BALANCED BUDGET
DEFICITS.
THEY ARE RUNNING A STRICT,
AUSTERE PROGRAM.bd
NEIL: I KNOW YOU WILL BE■■■■■■
THE BATTLE BETWEEN ALEXANDRIA
OCASIO CORTEZ AND BORDER PATROL
ERUPTING OVER NEW ALLEGATIONS
FACEBOOK POSTINGS THAT WERE
PRETTY OBNOXIOUS MIGHT HAVE
BEEN MORE OF THEM THAN WE
THOUGHT AND MORE INVOLVED IN
SAYING WHAT THEY SAY AFTER
THIS.
oing to
ta
ke care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
We're the Tenney's
and we're USAA members for life.
Call USAA to start saving
on insurance today.
I'M REALLY INTO THIS CAR,
and BUT HOW DO I KNOW IFor life.
I'M GETTING A GOOD DEAL?
I TELL TRUECAR MY ZIP
AND WHICH CAR I WANT
AND TRUECAR SHOWS
THE RANGE OF PRICES
PEOPLE IN MY AREA
ACTUALLYFOR THE SAME CAR
SO I KNOW IF I'M GETTING
A GREAT PRICE.
THIS IS HOW CAR BUYING
WAS ALWAYS MEANT TO BE.
THIS IS TRUECAR.
♪ Hoo
- I like to plan my
activities before I take trip,
so by the time I get there
I can just enjoy the ride.
With TripAdvisor,
and if you like what you see,
you can book it with ease.
■■■Just another way TripAdvisor
helps you make your trip
a masterpiece.
♪ Hoo
- Read reviews, check hotel
prices, book things to do.
TripAdvisor.
NEIL: DONALD TRUMP JUST TWEETED
DEMOCRATS MUST CHANGE THE
LOOPHOLE IN ASYLUM LAWS BUT
THEY PROBABLY WON'T, MASSIVE
CRIME AND DRUGS AS BORDER
PATROL TELLS FOX NEWS IT IS
LOOKING AT RECENT ALLEGATIONS
MAKING CONTROVERSIAL COMMENTS
AND MORE ABOUT LAWMAKERS, IN A
SECOND PRIVATE FACEBOOK GROUP
AND ONE THAT WAS TAKEN DOWN
LATER THAN THE FIRST ONE.
THE NATIONAL BORDER PATROL,
BRANDON JUDD, GOOD TO HAVE YOU.
DO YOU KNOW THE LATEST OF
FACEBOOK POSTINGS THAT INVOLVE
FORMER AGENTS THAN THE ORIGINAL
ROUNDUP THAT WAS CRITICAL OF
ILLEGALS BEING HELD AT THE
DETENTION CENTERS EVEN THOUGH
IT IS VISITING DETENTION
CENTERS?
>> A COUPLE FACEBOOK PAGES ARE
OUT THERE.
YOU HAVE SOME REAL CVP NATIONS
WAS ALWAYS FACEBOOK PAGES HAVE
BEEN CRITICAL OF ILLEGAL ALIENS
AND CERTAIN LAWMAKERS.
SOME THINGS ARE FINE, THERE'S
PLENTY OF POLITICAL TALK AND
YOU CAN DO THAT, ABSOLUTELY
REPREHENSIBLE AND I AM AWARE
THERE HAVE BEEN 13 LETTERS SENT
OUT TO EMPLOYEES THAT ARE CEASE
AND DESIST LETTERS, THEY NEED
TO STOP THEIR FACEBOOK POSTS
AND NOW THE INVESTIGATION HAS
TO GO INTO THE NATURE THAT
VIOLATES POLICY AND THEY NEED
TO BE HELD ACCOUNTABLE.
NEIL: DO YOU MEAN FIRED?
>> IT DEPENDS ON THE NATURE OF
THE POST.
IF THEY ARE RELEASING
INFORMATION ABOUT LAW
ENFORCEMENT INFORMATION, THEY
ARE VERY STRICT.
NEIL: WHAT ABOUT RACIST
COMMENTS?
>> RACIST COMMENTS, WE CANNOT
AS UNIFORM LAW ENFORCEMENT, WE
CANNOT SHOW THE WE HAVE A BIAS.
WE CANNOT PROPERLY ENFORCE THE
LAW.
THERE IS NO PLACE IN LAW
ENFORCEMENT FOR INDIVIDUALS
THAT ARE RACIST, NO PLACE IN
LAW ENFORCEMENT TO HATE OTHER
GROUPS OF PEOPLE BECAUSE YOU
CANNOT ENFORCE THE LAWS
PROPERLY IF YOU BRING THAT BIAS
INTO THE WORKPLACE.
NEIL: SENATOR CHUCK SCHUMER
CALLED FOR THE FIRING OF MARK
MORGAN, OF CUSTOMS AND BORDER
PROTECTION, ULTIMATELY PICKED
TO LEAD THE AGENCY BECAUSE OF
WHAT WAS HAPPENING UNDER HIM.
>> ABSOLUTELY WRONG.
COMMISSIONER MORGAN WHEN HE WAS
THERE, HE WAS AWARE OF ONE POST
AND IMMEDIATELY TOOK ACTION AND
TOOK THE MOST SEVERE ACTION HE
COULD TAKE UNDER LABOR LAWS AT
THAT TIME.
COMMISSIONER MORGAN DID WHAT HE
NEEDED TO DO.
SENATOR SCHUMER CALLED FOR
DETERMINATION BEFORE HE WAS THE
COMMISSIONER, AND CALL FOR HIS
TERMINATION.
SENATOR SCHUMER HAS A
COMPLETELY WRONG AND LOOK AT
THE PEOPLE WHO HAVE BEEN HERE A
LONG TIME, SHOULD HAVE BEEN
AWARE OF THIS AND SHOULD HAVE
TAKEN PROPER ACTION.
NEIL: I DON'T KNOW WHERE THE
TRUTH START AND EXAGGERATION
BEGINS ON FACEBOOK POSTINGS BUT
ONE THING POLITICO AND OTHERS
REPORTED IS HIGH REPS WERE MORE
AWARE OF THIS.
DO YOU KNOW ABOUT ANY OF IT?
>> THEY WERE AWARE OF THIS.
CVP IS REQUIRED TO MONITOR WHAT
AGENTS ARE DOING WHETHER IT IS
ON DUTY OR OFF DUTY.
FACEBOOK PAGES, THEY WERE AWARE
OF THESE PAGES.
NEIL: DID THEY TAKE IT DOWN?
>> IF YOU LOOK AT THESE
FACEBOOK PAGES THERE WERE A
GREAT MANY HIGH-LEVEL MANAGERS
ON THESE PAGES.
THEY WERE ABSOLUTELY AWARE OF
IT AND HAD A RESPONSIBILITY TO
DO SOMETHING AND DIDN'T.
I WILL POINT BACK TO 2017,
ALMOST TWO YEARS TO THE DATE,
THE NATIONAL BORDER PATROL
COUNCIL SENT AN ADVISORY TO
AGENTS TELLING THEM TO BE
CAREFUL WHAT YOU ARE POSTING ON
FACEBOOK, THERE ARE CERTAIN
THINGS YOU CAN POST, CERTAIN
THINGS THAT ARE ABSOLUTELY
INAPPROPRIATE AND COULD
POTENTIALLY AFFECT YOUR JOB
STATUS AND CVP DIDN'T FOLLOW
UP.
IF YOU LOOK AT THE FACEBOOK
POSTS, WE WERE THE FIRST TO
COME OUT AND CONDEMN THOSE
POSTS WHEN THE ARTICLE BROKE,
THE AGENCY CAME IN LATER IN
THIS HAPPENS ON A REGULAR BASIS
AND IT IS VERY FRUSTRATING.
WE WANT THE MOST HONORABLE
ORGANIZATIONS, AND WE ARE
CHARGED WITH DETERMINING THE
BORDER AND HAVE TO DO IT
PROPERLY.
>> THANK YOU FOR TAKING THE
TIME.
JOINING US OUT OF THE CITY.
MEANWHILE INNIA, THIS
IS RIDGECREST, NO REPORTS
SIGNIFJURIES.
AND THE SERVICE DIRECTOR, MORE
SERIOUS DAMAGE AS DAYLIGHT
EMERGES AND THEY Rq■■■q■q■■■q■U
EARTHQUAKE, AFTER 6.4 UDE
EARTHQUAKE THE DORE.
THAT IS TECHNICALLY 10 TIMES
MORE SERIOUS.
■ww■■■■
NEIL: WE JUST HEARD FROM BORDER
PATROL BRANDON JUDD, A DEMOCRAT
WHO ISN'T IMPRESSED WITH WHAT
HE'S HEARING FROM BORDER
OFFICIALS.
CONGRESSMAN OUR GREEN, GOOD TO
HAVE YOU.
YOUR THE CONGRESSMAN, THE BIG
CHEESE, LET ME GET YOUR TAKE ON
WHAT DAMAGE IT IS SAYING, IF HE
FINDS, THAT THESE OF NOXIOUS
COMMENTS, BORDER AGENTS HAVEN'T
CHARGED WITH ON THESE FACEBOOK
POSTS, HE WOULD ADVOCATE, IS
THAT GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOU?
>> IT IS GOOD ENOUGH.
I AM SURE OTHER THINGS NEED TO
BE DONE AS WELL BUT IF A PERSON
EXHIBITS RACIAL VIEWS THAT ARE
ABHORRENT, RACISM AS IT IS
CALLED BY THE AGENTS, I COMMEND
THEM.
IT IS APPROPRIATE TO CONSIDER
TERMINATING THE RELATIONSHIP.
NEIL: THIS MEASURE THAT WAS
APPROVED IN CONGRESS,
$4.6 MILLION FUNDING TO DEAL
WITH THE CRISIS AT THE BORDER,
DID YOU VOTE FOR THAT?
>> I DID.
LELAND: YOU DID SOLD TO EASE
THE CONGESTION OF THE PROBLEM
WITH THE KIDS?
>> I DID FOR A MULTIPLICITY OF
REASONS.
I UNDERSTAND WHY THOSE WHO
DIDN'T DID NOT DO SO.
I DID SO BECAUSE I HAVE BEEN
TALKING FOR SOME TIME ABOUT
CONDITIONS AT THE BORDER.
I SAW THE CONDITIONS AND I
WANTED TO DO WHAT I COULD TO BE
HELPFUL BUT I UNDERSTAND THOSE
WHO CHOSE NOT TO, HIGHLIGHT THE
FACT THERE NEEDS TO BE MORE
TRANSPARENCY AND
ACCOUNTABILITY.
I RESPECT WHAT THEY DID.
FOR ME, SEEING WHAT THEY DID
WITH HER FATHER ON THE SHORES
OF THE RIVER, TOUCHED MY HEART
IN A WAY THAT WAS IMPOSSIBLE
FOR ME TO VOTE OTHERWISE.
LELAND: THESE CHILDREN IN
MIGRANT CENTERS IS QUINTUPLE
WHAT IT WAS UNDER THESE
FACILITIES, BUT NOT PREPARED,
AND HOMELAND SECURITY.
>> THANK YOU FOR ASKING THE
QUESTION.
I HAVE A QUESTION THAT MIRRORS
AN ANSWER.
WE ARE THERE TO FACILITATE THE
LAW OR TO DETER PEOPLE FROM
COMING INTO THE COUNTRY?
IN THE EARLY PART OF THE 19TH
CENTURY WERE PROCESSING 5000
PEOPLE-10,000 PEOPLE A DAY,
NEVER SEPARATED CHILDREN FROM
THEIR PARENTS.
PERSONS WERE FLEEING
SCANDINAVIA AND EASTERN EUROPE
AND CAME BY THE MILLIONS AND WE
PROCESSED THEM.
DO WE WANT TO PROCESS PEOPLE
FIND A MEANS BY WHICH WE CAN
DETER THEM?
NEIL: THESE NUMBERS ARE
STAGGERING, MORPHING WHAT
BARACK OBAMA WAS DEALING WITH,
SEPARATING KIDS FROM FAMILIES
TO MAKE SURE THOSE WITH WHOM WE
WERE TRAVELING WERE RELATED?
>> COMPARED TO THOSE COMING
THROUGH ELLIS ISLAND THEY ARE
NOT DWARFING THEM ESPECIALLY
GIVEN --
LELAND: RIGHT AT THE BORDER, IT
IS A DIFFERENT DAY RIGHT HERE,
RIGHT NOW.
DO YOU THINK THE $4.6 BILLION
IS ALLOCATED TO DEAL WITH --
WOULD YOU BE HAPPY THE SAME
FOLKS OR DO YOU WANT SOMEONE
ELSE?
>> I HAVE TO SAY THIS.
THOSE COMING THROUGH ELLIS
ISLAND, RIGHT THERE, RIGHT
THEN, WE WELCOME THEM.
THERE SEEMS TO BE A REMOVAL OF
THE WELCOME MAT.
NEIL: WE WELCOME THEM BECAUSE
THERE WERE ASSURANCES OF FAMILY
OR FRIENDS WHO COULD TAKE THEM
IN AND TAKE CARE OF THEM AND
NOT THE UNITED STATES
GOVERNMENT.
>> A GOOD MANY OF THEM DID NOT.
THEY HAVE FAMILY, FRIENDS WHO
COULD ASSIST THEM AS WELL BUT
WE ARE TURNING THEM AWAY
WITHOUT GIVING THEM ENERGY TO A
CERTAIN EXTENT BY PUSHING THE
INTERVIEW PROCESS TO MEXICO.
TO YOUR QUESTION ABOUT WHETHER
THE PERSONS IN CHARGE WHO
SHOULD REMAIN IN CHARGE, IT IS
MY OPINION THAT PERSONS IN
CHARGE ARE VICTIMS THEMSELVES
BECAUSE THEY ARE FORCED TO
ENFORCE POLICIES THAT QUITE
FRANKLY ARE ABHORRENT.
THE POLICY OF SEPARATING
CHILDREN FROM THEIR PARENTS, NO
COUNTRY SHOULD HAVE SUCH
POLICY.
NEIL: YOU CAN UNDERSTAND WHY IT
HAPPENED.
WHEN BARACK OBAMA -- HE SIMPLY
DIDN'T KNOW WHERE KIDS WERE
COMING FROM.
HE DIDN'T FORMALLY SEPARATE
THEM FROM AN EXTENDED PERIOD OF
TIME BUT RECOGNIZED SOME OF
THEM IS USED AS LEVERAGE TO GET
INTO THIS COUNTRY.
>> YOU AMONG ANY FOLKS HAVE
SOMETHING THAT IS NOT
APPROPRIATE BUT THE
OVERWHELMING MAJORITY OF THESE
PEOPLE ARE COMING HERE TO
ESCAPE PERSECUTION, ESCAPE
CRIME.
I JUST RETURNED FROM EL
SALVADOR TO BRING BACK A
CONSTITUENT WHO HAD BEEN
DEPORTED.
WE BROUGHT HIM HOME, HE HAD A
10 YEAR BAR, HE WAS MARRIED TO
AN AMERICAN WOMAN, HAD TWO
AMERICAN CHILDREN, HE REPORTED
TO ICE AND WAS DEPORTED WITH
MONEY IN HIS POCKET AND CLOTHES
ON HIS BACK.
WE BROUGHT HIM HOME.
IT IS THE ATTITUDE WE HAVE TO
DEAL WITH.
LET ME THANK YOU FOR GIVING ME
THE OPPORTUNITY TO SAY THAT
BECAUSE WE ARE FINDING IT IS
DIFFICULT TO GET THAT MESSAGE
OUT.
NEIL: I APPRECIATE YOU COMING
ON.
WE HAVE A COMMERCIAL COMING.
I WANT TO THANK YOU.
MUCH MORE AFTER THIS.
SFX: Record scratch
MUSIC (plays throughout):
[ 'Watch Me Walk'
by Spencer Ludwig ]
Yo DJ, can I put
in a request?
♪ Don't have
no sass about this ♪
♪ I'm on my way
I'm on my way ♪
♪ Can't take no class
about this ♪
♪ I'm on my way I'm on my ♪
♪ Like this! ♪
To start your investment plan,
This is a moment you plan for.
find an advisor at
MassMutual.com
SFX: [ Mnemonic ]
No matter what I wore, I worried
someone might see
my bladder leak ■n■n?n■n■nSon
To Always Discreet Boutique.
Its shape-hugging threads smooth
out the back.
So it fits better than Depend.
And no one notices.
Always Discreet.
You cast.
Audible reintroduced this
whole world to me.
So many great stories
from amazing people.
It makes me want
to be better.
To be able to connect with
the people's stories
that I'm listening to.
Thpiration.
on during my commute,■l the ti
Doing the dishes.
Working out.
While I'm in the car.
At bed time.
An Audible listener
is someone that
wants to broaden
their mind.
People who are
tired of listening
to the radio, or music.
To hear her speak
those words.
It was incredible.
■ievable.
there's something for almost
every taste in there.
Everything you777 to hea.
I signed up for gettingalmost
ea credit every month,
and I started exploring books
that I normally wouldn't read.
Our ability to empathize
through these stories,
tories,
can formational.
It's m■that
Audible can do for you.çcço
Just text Listen14
to 500500.
NEIL: WE ARE GETTING UPDATED
IMAGES FROM CALIFORNIA, THE 7.1
MAGNITUDE EARTHQUAKE, 10 TIMES
MORE SEVERE THAN THE ONE THAT
PRECEDED IT.
JEFF PAUL HAS THE LATEST.
IN RIDGECREST, CALIFORNIA.
>> Reporter: THIS EARTHQUAKE
WAS FELT FAR AND WIDE.
WE ARE NEAR THE EPICENTER OF
THE 7.1 EARTHQUAKE.
THERE ARE REPORTS OF PEOPLE AS
FAR NORTH AS SACRAMENTO AND AS
FAR EAST AS PHOENIX, ARIZONA
AND AS FAR SOUTH AS MEXICO,
FEELING SOME SORT OF RUMBLING
DUE TO THIS PARTICULAR
EARTHQUAKE RUMBLING AFTER 8:00.
UCER SHOT, THERE WAS FIRST Y
A SMALLER AFTERSHOCK THAT WAS
JUST MINOR BUT A FEW MINUTES
LATER THAT 7.1 MAGNITUDE
EARTHQUAKE RUMBLED THROUGH.
YOU COULD HEAR THINGS CRASHING
IN THE RESTAURANT.
YOU COULD HEAR PEOPLE SCREAMING
AS THEY TRY TO TAKE COVER OR
ñ■ñ■Y AND SHORTLY AFTER
THAT IF YOU GOT YOUR WITS ABOUT
YOU WE STARTED HEARING THE
SIRENS, OING EVERY
DIRECTION, AMBULANCES TRYING TO
RESPOND TO THE FLURRY OF CALLS
THEY GOT AFTER THIS EARTHQUAKE
AND FIRE IN THE DI AND AT
LEAST ONE STRUCTURE DESTROYED
AND A FEW OTHER FIRES, LIKELY
DO TO GAS LINE RUPTURES AND A
BIG PART OF THAT, BECAUSE OF
THE UNEASINESS OF RESIDENTS
SOME ARE CHOOSING TO SLEEP
OUTSIDE, WE CAUGHT UP WITH ONE
RESIDENT, HOW SHE IS LIVING HER
LIFE MOVING FORWARD.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> IF IT HAPPENS IT HAPPENS BUT
I'M NOT GOING TO SIT AROUND AND
NOT DO ANYTHING.@
I AM NOT GOING TO DO THAT, JUST
GOING TO GET ON WITH LIFE AND
IF IT HITS IT HITS.
THERE IS NOTHING I CAN DO TO
STOP IT, NOTHING I CAN DO TO
FOREWARN ME SO I GOT TO KEEP
BUSY SO I DON'T THINK ABOUT IT.
>> THERE WILL BE MORE
AFTERSHOCKS AND THERE'S A
CHANCE THERE COULD BE AN EVEN
BIGGER EARTHQUAKE ON THE WAY.
HEATHER: BE SAFE YOUR SELF IN
THE MIDDLE OF THAT.
YOUR KEEPING AN EYE ON IRAN
WHICH THREATENED TO RETALIATE,
ONE OF ITS TAKERS SEIZED BY THE
BRITISH, SEEING A BRITISH
TANKER.
■@■@■@
This is the couple who
wanted to get away
■
who used Expedia to book
the vacation rental
which led to the discovery
that sometimes
can lift you right up.
Expedia.
Everything you need to go.
Let's be honest,
you only talk about
your insurance
when you complain about it.
(garbled)....it's so painful.
Good point!
That's why Esurance is making
the whole experience
surprisingly painless.
So, you never have
to talk about it.
surprisingly painless.
Unless you're their
spokesperson.
Esurance. It's surprisingly
painless.
>>  ALL RIGHT.
FAST MOVING DEVELOPMENTS ON IRAN
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S DEMANDING THE UNITED
KINGDOM RELEASE THE OIL TANKER
IT SEIZED I BELIEVE IN
GIBRALTER.
AND THEY WILL NOT TALK.
AND COMMANDER, THE SOON TO BE
OUT GOING PRIME MINISTER,
THERESA MAY, TO WHATEVER IRAN IS
PLANNING AND PUSHING FOR THE
FULL DENUCLEARIZATION.
AND JUDGING WHAT HAPPENS NEXT.
YOU KNOW THIS REGION VERY, VERY
WELL AND YOU KNOW WHAT THE
IRANIANS MIGHT BE CONSIDERING.
THEY'RE NOT AVERSE TO SEIZING
PERSONNEL OF THE REGION AS THEY
DID BACK IN 2007, WHEN THEY
STORMED THE BRITISH FRIGATE AND
I BELIEVE HELD ABOUT A DOZEN MEN
AND WOMEN CAPTIVE FOR A WHILE
BEFORE RELEASING THEM.
THEY'RE UP TO THAT AND
APPARENTLY ITCHING TO DO THAT OR
THE SAME KIND OF THING, WHAT DO
YOU THINK?
>> I THINK, NEIL, THE
SIGNIFICANT DEVELOPMENT IN THE
FACT THAT THE BRITISH DECIDED TO
SEIZE THIS TANKER.
CLEARLY, IT WAS IN VIOLATION,
NOT JUST OF U.S. SANCTIONS, BUT
MORE IMPORTANTLY, EU SANCTIONS
WITH THAT OIL HEADED TOWARDS
SYRIA.
THAT OIL TANKER CARRIES TWO
MILLION BARRELS OF OIL WHICH
EQUATES TO ABOUT 84 MILLION
GALLONS.
THAT WAS HUGE FOR THE SYRIAN
REGIME TO BE ABLE TO SUPPORT
ITSELF AND THE FACT THAT IT'S
CUT OFF IS GOOD.
WHAT ION RAH DOES NEXT, I THINK
THEY SHOULD CHOOSE VERY WISELY
BECAUSE THEY DO NOT WANT TO
ACCIDENTALLY START SOMETHING
THEY MAY NOT BE ABLE TO STOP OR
CONTROL.
NEIL: ALL RIGHT, WE UNDERSTAND,
I MIGHT HAVE MISSPOKE,
COMMANDER, THAT THIS
CONVERSATION BETWEEN THE
PRESIDENT AND THERESA MAY WAS
ACTUALLY YESTERDAY.
THE DETAILS ABOUT IT ARE ONLY
COMING TO LIGHT TODAY, BUT THEY
DID TALK ABOUT SHARED INTEREST
IN ENFORCING SANCTIONS ON SYRIA
TO ENSURE THAT IRAN DOESN'T
OBTAIN A NUCLEAR WEAPON.
WITH THE IRANIANS READY TO
EXCEED PRODUCTION, THAT WOULD
MAKE SUCH A THING MORE LIKELY,
THEY'RE NOT PAYING ATTENTION.
>> WELL, WHEN YOU LOOK AT IT,
IRAN IS GETTING SQUEEZED, MUCH
QUICKER AND HARSHER THAN
ANTICIPATED WHEN PRESIDENT TRUMP
PUT THE SANCTIONS BACK INTO
PLACE.
IF THEY BREAK THE CAP THEY CLAIM
THEY HAVE WITH RESPECT TO THE
AMOUNT THEY'RE ALLOWED TO HAVE
FOR ENRICHED URANIUM, THEY'RE IN
VIOLATION OF THE AGREEMENT.
THAT NOW MOVES THINGS INTO A
DIFFERENT CATEGORY, AND THERE IS
A LETTER BY SENATORS CRUZ AND
RUBIO AND I BELIEVE ONE OTHER,
NOW THAT THEY VIOLATE THAT
AGREEMENT WE'RE NOW INTO THE
U.N. CATEGORY WHERE THE
SNAP-BACK SANCTIONS CAN NOW COME
INTO PLACE.
THIS IS NOW ENGAING THE WHOLE
WORLD.
IRAN IS NOT JUST AGAINST THE
U.S. AT THIS POINT, THEY'RE NOW
AGAINST THE WORLD.
WHEN IRAN IS DOING THAT, THEY'RE
GOING TO FIND THEMSELVES
INCREASINGLY ISOLATED, NOT JUST
FROM THE U.S. ABOUT YOU ALSO OUR
EUROPEAN ALLIES ARE GOING TO
REALIZE THEY NEED TO NOT ONLY
SUPPORT THE U.S., BUT MORE
IMPORTANTLY, SUPPORT THE U.N. IN
WHAT WE'RE DOING TO ENSURE THAT
IRAN NEVER DEVELOPS THAT WEAPONS
CAPABILITY.
>> AND EVERYONE IS WAITING TO
SEE WHAT THEY'LL DO IN
RESPONDENT TO THIS MOVE.
I MENTIONED IN 2007, SEIZING OF
THAT THE IRANIAN CLAIMS WASN'T
IN INTERNATIONAL WATER, WHEN IT
COMES TO THE STRAIT OF HORMUZ OR
ANYTHING CLOSE, THEY STATE THAT
THAT'S THEIR LAND, OR THEIR
WATER.
HOW DID YOU LOOK AT
INTERNATIONAL STANDARDS 12 MILES
FROM A SHORE IS EVERYBODY'S
WATER.
>> IT'S INTERNATIONAL WATERWAYS,
AND RECOGNIZED UNDER NANE
INTERNATIONAL LAW.
WHILE THE IRANIANS MAKE THAT
CLAIM, THERE'S NO WEIGHT WHEN IT
COMES TO THAT INTERNATIONAL
STANDARD.
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO CONTINUE TO
TRANSIT THAT WATERWAY AND IF
IRAN DOES INTERFERE WITH IT,
THEN THE INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY
AT THAT POINT HAVE AN OBLIGATION
TO DO WHATEVER IT TAKES,
DIPLOMATICALLY, ECONOMICALLY AND
IF NECESSARILY, MILITARILY TO
ENSURE THAT THE WATERWAY IS OPEN
FOR THE PRE TRANSIT OF OIL TO
KEEP THE ECONOMIES GOING.
>> COMMANDER, THANK YOU VERY,
VERY MUCH, GOOD CHATTING WITH
YOU AGAIN.
>> AS ALWAYS, NEIL.
THANK YOU.
>> WE HAVE NOT FORGOTTEN ABOUT
THE 2020 RACE, THE DEMOCRATS ARE
KNEE DEEP IN FUND RAISING AND A
LOT KNEE DEEP IN CASH, WHO HAS
THE MOST?
IT'S A LITTLE EARLY IN THE
PROCESS, BUT NEVER TOO EARLY TO
START PICKING UP THE NUMBERS AND
GILLIAN TURNER WITH THE LATEST.
>> GOOD MORNING, NEIL.
THE COMPETITION FOR FUNDS, AS
YOU SAID, IS STUFF THIS ELECTION
CYCLE AND IT'S TIGHTER AMONG THE
TOP TIER DEMOCRATS DURING THE
SECOND QUARTER OF THIS YEAR
ACCORDING TO THE NEW NUMBERS.
CANDIDATES ARE ON DEADLINE TO
REPORT BY JULY 15TH, BUT MOST
MADE IT IN UNDER THE GUN.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
SO FAR PETE BUTTIGIEG COMES IN
TOPS AT 24.8 MILLION DOLLARS IN
HAUL.
JOE BIDEN UP NEXT WITH 21.5
MILLION DOLLARS AND THEN BERNIE
SANDERS WITH 18 MILLION,
FOLLOWED BY KAMALA HARRIS WITH
12 MILLION.
AFTER HARRIS THOUGH THE DROP-OFF
IS PRETTY STEEP.
MICHAEL BENNETT NEXT WITH A 2.8
MILLION DOLLAR HAUL.
AND SAYS, HE'S FEELING THE HEAT.
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT FOR A LONG TIME.
I JUST GOT IN THE RACE SO WHAT
I'M CONCERNED ABOUT IS MAKING
SURE THAT WE CONTINUE TO RAISE
THE RESOURCES WE NEED TO BE ABLE
TO BE COMPETITIVE IN THE EARLY
STATES OF IOWA AND NEW
HAMPSHIRE.
>> SO THESE NUMBERS MATTER,
NEIL, BECAUSE THE CANDIDATES
WILL ALL NEED EVERY DOLLAR THEY
CAN GET IN ORDER TO MAKE IT TO
ROUND TWO.
THE NEXT DEMOCRATIC DEBATES ARE
COMING UP SOON.
THE OTHER THING THAT MATTERS
HERE, POPULARITY.
BIDEN STILL TEN POINTS AHEAD OF
HIS DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES EVEN
AFTER FALLING A LITTLE IN THE
POLLS AFTER THE LAST DEBATE LAST
WEEK.
NEIL.
THANK YOU VERY, VERY MUCH.
WE'RE KEEPING TRACK WHERE THE
CANDIDATES ARE GOING TO BE.
JOE BIDEN, WE UNDERSTAND IS
GOING TO SPEND A GOOD CHUNK OF
TIME IN SOUTH CAROLINA,
CONSIDERED A MUST-WIN FOR HIM TO
STABILIZE THE CAMPAIGN THAT'S
BEEN BUFFETED LATELY.
SENATOR, GOOD TO HAVE YOU.
>> GOOD MORNING, NEIL, GOOD TO
BE BACK WITH YOU.
>> JOE BIDEN IS GOING TO BE IN
YOUR BEAUTIFUL STATE TODAY.
HE'S TALKED TO THE PRESS SINCE
THAT DEBATE WHERE HE'S BEEN SORT
OF UNIVERSALLY PANNED.
HE CAN RIGHT THE SHIP.
HE'S LOOKING FORWARD, NOT
LOOKING BACKWARD.
HOW DOES HE LOOK IN YOUR STATE
DEMOCRATIC
>> YOU KNOW, FOR MY FRIEN ON■■■
THEv>■>w■w■w■w■■■w■w■■>■■■■■■■
CANDIDATE THEY THINK IS THEÑáw■T
COMPETITIVE AGAINST OUR PRESIDE
AFRICAN-AMERICAN VOTERS AREçççç
MAJORITY IN T■■■RIMARY
ANççççççççççççççççççççççççççççç
AGAIN, JOE  ESPECIALLY
A RACIAL ISSUE LIKE BUSING, HAS
PROMPTED MORE FOLKS TO START
TAKING A SECOND LOOK AT HER AND
SHE IS NOW GAINING WHAT'S BEEN
THE STATE--
SHE'S BEEN BEHIND IN THE
AFRICAN-AMERICAN COMMUNITY WHICH
IS QUITE UNUSUAL AND
INTERESTING, AND JOE BIDEN'S
LEGACY AS A FIRST VICE-PRESIDENT
OF THE FIRST AFRICAN-AMERICAN
PRESIDENT HAS SERVED HIM WELL,
BUT THOSE NUMBERS ARE STARTING
TO SHOW A LOT OF CRACKS.
>> YOU KNOW, AS YOU'VE REMINDED
ME IN THE PAST, I THOUGHT YOU
WERE TALKING ABOUT SOUTH
CAROLINA IN YOUR PRIDE OF BEING
A SENATOR THERE.
BUT IT'S TURNED A LOT TO RACISM
IN THE PAST, THERE THAT GEORGE
--
TO THE RACE IN THE PAST, AND
THERE THAT GEORGE BUSH, AND JOHN
MCCAIN, PUTTING HIM ASIDE IN
SOUTH CAROLINA, WE SAW SOMETHING
SIMILAR WITH BARACK OBAMA, A
CANDIDATE WHO HAD TO WIN AT THAT
TIME.
I'M WONDERING IF IT'S A SIMILAR
THIS GO ROUND?
>> I'M CALLING IT THE MOMENTUM,
THE FIRST, IN THE PRIMARY STATE,
SOUTH CAROLINA, PROVEN TO BE THE
SPRINGBOARD FOR PRESIDENTIAL
SUCCESS ON THE RIGHT AS WELL AS
THE LEFT.
AND I THINK BACK SINCE 1980,
SOUTH CAROLINANS HAVE CHOSEN ON
THE REPUBLICANS SIDE AND ON THE
DEMOCRATIC SIDE, A LOT OF
SUCCESS AS WELL.
I THINK THAT SOUTH CAROLINA IS
POISED TO MAKE THE DECISION FOR
THE DEMOCRATS THIS CYCLE.
IT WILL BE INTERESTING TO SEE
WHO THEY CHOOSE.
I STILL THINK THEY'RE A LONG
WAY, OF COURSE, FROM 2020, BUT
IT WILL BE VERY INTERESTING TO
SEE WHO WILL STAND TOE TO TOE
WITH PRESIDENT TRUMP.
I LIKE OUR ODDS RIGHT NOW, BY
THE WAY.
WE'RE IN A VERY GOOD POSITION,
OUR ECONOMY IS STRONG EAR
INTERNATIONAL AND NO DOUBT WHEN
YOU LOOK AT THE 2020 ELECTION,
IT'S GOING TO BE A STRONG,
POWERFUL MATCH-UP.
RIGHT NOW I'M EXCITED WHERE WE
ARE.
NEIL: SENATOR, IT'S EARLY AND
YOU REMIND ME IT'S VERY EARLY SO
DON'T GET FIXATED ON POLLS.
GIVEN THE STRENGTH OF THE
ECONOMY AND THE UNEXPECTED
224,000 JOB SURGE IN THE LATEST
MONTH AND MARKETS IN AND OUT OF
ALL-TIME HIGHS, THAT THE
PRESIDENT ISN'T BENEFITTING MORE
FROM THAT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS HAPPENING?
>> WELL, WE'RE AT A VERY
POLARIZED PLACE FROM A POLITICAL
PERSPECTIVE CALLED AMERICA.
IT'S BEEN CHALLENGING FOR A VERY
LONG TIME, IT'S BEEN GETTING
WORSE INCREMENTALLY.
THERE'S NO DOUBT WE'VE HAD
DISTRACTIONS FROM WHAT SHOULD
BE, IT'S THE ECONOMY, STUPID.
THE PROGRESS HE'S MADE, AND
ESPECIALLY IN THE FRAGILE
ECONOMIC AMERICANS, WE WOULD BE
CELEBRATED 6 MILLION JOBS
CREATED SINCE THE TAX REFORM.
HALF HAVE BEEN OCCUPIED BY
AFRICAN-AMERICANS AND HISPANICS.
WE HAVE A LOT TO CELEBRATE, BUT
THERE HAVE BEEN SO MANY
DISTRACTIONS THAT IF YOU FOCUS
ON■■■ATTERSVERAGE
WHAT'S MYbs■@sbsUCbs
IN THIS OMY?
CAN MY KIDSXP BETTER
BUT THE NARE HEAR RT
CONSISTENTLY HAS NOT RE WITH TH
THAT  UNFORTUNATELY,
DIST LOT
■ IN FA■■■
GRCONOMY S■■■■■
DES.
WE'VE SE PRO
M
FIRSTS THAN WE'VE EVER SEEN.
WE SHOULD BE EXCITED TO BE
AMERICANS AND WE SHOULD BE
EXCITED TO BE AMERICANS RIGHT
NOW IN 2019 AND THERE'S SO MANY
DISTRACTIONS, TRYING TO DIVIDE
US.
BECAUSE, IF WE STAND UNITED WE
WIN.
IF WE ARE DIVIDED, WE ARE IN
JEOPARDY.
I THINK WE'RE GOING TO GET OUR
ACT TOGETHER AND I THINK THAT
THE LEFT HAS BEEN SELLING A
RHETORIC AS IF IT WERE REALITY
AND WE'RE GOING TO BE ABLE TO
DISCERN THE DIFFERENCE AND
CREATE THE CONTRAST SO THAT THE
AVERAGE AMERICANS, WHETHER THEY
VOTE FOR REPUBLICANS OR NOT,
THAT'S NOT THE QUESTION.
IS AMERICA BETTER OFF UNDER THE
CONSERVATIVE PRINCIPLES AND
POLICIES PUT IN PLACE?
THE ANSWER IS RESOUNDINGLY YES.
NEIL: BUT DO YOU THINK THE
PRESIDENT RISKS TORPEDOING THIS
WITH THE ONGOING TRADE RIFT WITH
CHINA.
THE TARIFFS HAVEN'T HAD A CHANCE
TO KICK IN.
SO MANY ON STORE SHELVES.
THEY WERE GOING TO KICK IN.
THE IMPACT HASN'T BEEN FELT.
AND THE PRESIDENT ARGUES HE
LIKES TARIFFS ANYWAY, AVERAGE
AMERICANS PAY THOSE TARIFFS AND
I'M WONDERING IF YOU FEEL HE'S
OUT OF STEP WITH THAT OR OUT OF
SINK WITH THAT AND IT'S GOING TO
COST HIM?
>> WELL, I'D LIKE TO BREAK THE
TARIFF CONVERSATION INTO
MULTIPLE CATEGORIES.
YOU THINK ABOUT CHINA.
CHINA'S GOAL IS TO STEAL THE
FUTURE WHICH WOULD  IMPERIL
AMERICA'S PROGRESS.
THIS IS TO RESTORE CONFIDENCE IN
OUR WORK FORCE AND TO CREATE THE
BEST FUTURE GOING FORWARD FROM A
TECHNOLOGICAL STANDPOINT.
THEIR GOAL WITH THE INTELLECTUAL
THEFT--
>> DO YOU THINK THAT TARIFFS ARE
A GOOD THING, PERIOD.
IF IT DOESN'T SETTLE IT'S GOING
TO BOOMERANG ON REPUBLICANS?
>> WERE YOU TALKING ABOUT THE
SIX OR SEVEN STATES, THE WAGE
GAUGE, THAT TARIFFS COULD PUT IN
JEOPARDY.
THEIR WAGE GROWTH HAS
OUTSTRIPPED THE WAGE GROWTH.
SOME HAD 4, 5, 6% WAGE GROWTH.
THAT'S EXCITING ESPECIALLY IN
THOSE SECTORS.
THE TRUTH IS THE OVERALL TARIFF
CONVERSATION IS NOT IN THE
OVERALL INTEREST OF MOST
AMERICANS, NO QUESTION.
I PUT THE AS SISTER  -- ASTERISK
WHEN YOU PUT IT OUT THERE WE
HAVE TO MAKE SURE WE DON'T GO
TOO FAR, THE 232 AUTO TARIFF IS
A CLASSIC EXAMPLE WHERE I HAVE
PUSHED BACK BECAUSE I THINK IT
CREATES HEADWINDS THROUGHOUT THE
SOUTH.
NEIL: ALWAYS A PLEASURE CATCHING
UP WITH YOU.
BE WELL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
NEIL: SENATOR SCOTT OUT OF SOUT
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION BAC20■■ CE
IS THAT EVEN LEGAL AFTER THIS?
■
BEING DETECTED WAS
NOT AN OPTION.
IF I WAS RECOGNIZED
THE WHOLE OPERATION
WAS BLOWN.
THE ELEMENT OF
SURPRISE WAS IMPERATIVE.
WOW. HE WON'T EVEN
RECOGNIZE YOU.
SERIOUSLY. I DON'T
EVEN RECOGNIZE MYSELF.
AND THANKS TO MY
CASHREWARDS CREDIT CARD
FROM NAVY FEDERAL
WITH NEVER-EXPIRING REWARDS
IT'S GONNA BE
A KILLER HONEYMOON.
WOO!
MAUI!!
BOOM
VY FEDERAL CREDIT UNIOqOqO
OUR MEMBERS,
ARE THE MISSION.
>>  AN EXECUTIVE ORDER ON THE
CENSUS?
>> WE'RE THINKING ABOUT DOING
THAT.
THAT'S ONE OF THE WAYS.
THERE ARE FOUR OR FIVE WAYS TO
DO IT.
WE CAN ADD ON AN ADDITION.
PRINTING NOW AND ADD AN ADDENDUM
AFTER WE GET A POSITIVE
DECISION.
WE'RE WORKING ON A LOT OF
THINGS, INCLUDING AN EXECUTIVE
ORDER.
NEIL: THE PRESIDENT IS LOOKING
FOR WAYS HE'S ADDING THE
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION AFTER ALL
INCLUDING AS HE SAID AN
EXECUTIVE ORDER.
WILL IT HOLD UP IN COURT?
WHO BETTER TO PICK IT APART THAN
ATTORNEY EXTRAORDINARE,
MERCEDES.
>> NEIL.
NEIL: THE SUPREME COURT DIDN'T
REJECT THE ARGUMENT AS MUCH AS
SAY THE ADMINISTRATION THROUGH
THE COMMERCE DEPARTMENT DIDN'T
GIVE IT A COMPELLING ENOUGH
CASE.
>> AND DIDN'T GIVE THE
EXPLANATION.
I'M HEADED BACK TO 2013.
THERE WAS A SIMILAR CASE HAVING
TO DO.
IT HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THIS,
BUT THAT LAW.
THE CHIEF JUSTICE ROBERTS SAID
WE'RE GOING TO STEP AWAY.
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT IS GOING
TO STEP AWAY AND LET THE STATES
DEAL WITH THE LEGISLATIVE
PROCESS AND THEY CAN DEAL AT THE
LOCAL LEVEL.
BASICALLY THE GOVERNANCE OF THE
FEDERAL PART STEPPED BACK.
NOW, 2019.
NOW THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT STEPS
IN AND SAYS, HEY, WE WANT TO
HELP WITH RESPECT TO THE VOTING
RIGHTS ACT, WHICH, WHAT IT DID
WAS MADE SURE THAT THE
INDIVIDUALS COULD VOTE,
REGARDLESS OF DISCRIMINATION.
SO THEY NEED TO GO BACK DECADES
AGO.
IT STARTED WITH ALLOWING
INDIVIDUALS TO VOTE REGARDLESS
OF THEIR RACE.
NOW, SO THE CHIEF JUSTICE
ROBERTS SAYS, WHY ARE YOU GOING
BACK TO THE VOTING RIGHTS ACT.
LET THE STATES DEAL WITH IT.
WHY ARE THEY STEPPING IN IN 2019
AND WE'RE GOING TO ASSIST IN THE
PROMULGATION OF THE VOTING
RIGHTS ACT AP MAKE SURE THERE'S
NO DISCRIMINATION AND MAKE SURE
THAT THE DISTRICTS THAT HAVE A
HIGH NUMBER OF INDIVIDUALS THAT
ARE OF COLOR HAVE THE
APPROPRIATE NUMBERS OF
REPRESENTATION IN CONGRESS.
WHEN WE'VE ALREADY RULED THAT
THE STATES CAN DEAL WITH IT.
>> SO WHAT KIND OF COMPELLING
ARGUMENT DID THEY NEED TO MAKE
TO WIN OVER THIS PARTICULAR
JUDGE WHO ASKED TO BE RIGHT
OVER.
>> WE WANT THEM TO LOOK AT THE
DISTRICTING.
IT'S NOT DISCRIMINATION BECAUSE
WE KNOW, CHIEF JUDGE, YOU RULED
ON LETTING THE LOCAL GOVERNMENT
RULE ON THIS.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR APPROPRIATE
LEVELS OF REPRESENTATION.
AND IF WE LOOK AT THE DISTRICTS,
A LOT OF G.O.P. MEMBERS HAVE
WROTE ABOUT IN OP-ED.
WHY DON'T YOU COME FORWARD AND
SAY WE MIGHT NEED THIS, GREATER
NUMBERS OF REPRESENTATION.
IN ORDER FOR THEM TO BE GREATER
NUMBERS OF REPRESENTATION IN
CONGRESS OR LESS, WE NEED TO
KNOW HOW MANY U.S. CITIZENS ARE
IN PARTICULAR JURISDICTIONS
AROUND THE COUNTRY.
NEIL: SO WHY WASN'T THERE--
IT WAS TAKEN OUT.
THERE USED TO BE A STAPLE IN THE
CENSUS AND IT WAS TAKEN OUT BY
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION AND I
DON'T REMEMBER ANYBODY SAYING
BOO THEN.
THE CHIEF JUDGE WANTS TO SAY,
YES, IT WAS ABOUT DISTRICTING.
AND IT'S NOT JUST THE
DISTRICTING ISSUE WITH YOU
INFRASTRUCTURE.
980 BILLION DOLLARS YOU'RE GOING
TO GIVE AROUND THE COUNTRY.
NEIL: AND SOMETHING SINISTER
AFOOT HERE, THEY WANT TO PROVE
OR DISPROVE THAT.
>> ESPECIALLY WITH THE VOTING
RIGHTS ACT.
WE GET THE SAME JUDGE.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
>> CAN I SAY A QUICK HI TO MY
MOM, HI, ROSALYN.
HI, MOM.
SHE'S AMAZING.
NEIL: AND A FORMER DIRECTOR, HIS
READ ON THIS AND WHAT IT MEANS
IF THE PRESIDENT CAN'T GET THIS
QUESTION IN AFTER THIS.
ks lik
still nervous about buying
a new house.
ks lik
Is it that obvious?
Yes it is.
You know, maybe you'd worry less
if you got GEICO to help with
your homeowners insurance.
I didn't know GEICO could helps
with homeowners insurance.
Yep,
they've been doing it for years.
■
What are you doing?
Big Steve?
■@■@■@.p.p
■@There he is.
Big Steve?
Get to know GEICO and see
how much you could save on
homeowners and
renters insurance.
♪ Hoo
- I like to plan my
activities before I take trip,
so by the time I get there
I can just enjoy the ride.
With TN#or,
it's easy to discover ovx/000 b,
from walking tours in Rome
to wine tastings in Tuscany,
and if you like what you see,
you can book it with ease.
■g■  Juer way TripAdvisor
helps you make your trip
a masterpiece.
♪ Hoo
- Read reviews, check hotel
prices, book things to do.
TripAdvisor.
>>  ALL RIGHT.
WE'VE GOT TOM HOLMAN HERE, THE
FORMER ACTING ICE DIRECTOR.
HE'S GOING TO TALK ABOUT WHAT
THE ADMINISTRATION HAS TO GO
THROUGH WITH THE DEPORTATIONS.
MORE IN A SEC.
I WANT TOM TO TALK ABOUT WHAT
MERCEDES WAS TALKING ABOUT
REGARDING THE QUESTION IN THE
CENSUS THE ADMINISTRATION WANTS
TO PUSH BY EXECUTIVE ORDER TO
MAKE SURE YOU CAN STILL ASK, ARE
YOU A LEGAL CITIZEN OF THE
UNITED STATES.
WHERE DO YOU THINK THIS IS
GOING, TOM?
>> I HOPE THE ADMINISTRATION
SUCCEEDS IN IT FOR A COUPLE OF
REASONS.
NUMBER ONE, DON'T WE WANT TO
KNOW HOW MANY ILLEGAL ALIENS ARE
IN THE UNITED STATES?
AND IF THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT
IMMIGRATION REFORM, FREE MEDICAL
CARE, YOU KNOW, PATH WAYS TO
CITIZENSHIP FOR PEOPLE HERE
ILLEGALLY FOR A WHILE.
DON'T WE WANT TO KNOW WHO THAT
POPULATION IS?
I WOULD THINK THAT'S A WAY TO
MAKE EASY DECISION.
I DON'T THINK THAT
REPRESENTATIONS IN THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES OR ELECTORAL
COLLEGE THAT ELECTS OUR
PRESIDENT SHOULD BE BASED ON
PEOPLE HERE ILLEGALLY.
I THINK IT'S GOOD FOR A COUPLE
OF REASONS.
NEIL: SO, LET ME SWITCH GEARS A
LITTLE BIT HERE.
REGARDLESS HOW THAT WORKS.
THE ADMINISTRATION STILL SAYS,
IT'S GOING TO PURSUE THESE
DEPORTATIONS, LEGAL
DEPORTATIONS, THE KIND THAT WENT
UNDER BARACK OBAMA IN CASES
ALREADY ADJUDICATED AND ASK THAT
YOU GO BACK TO MEXICO, HONDURAS,
GUATEMALA, WHEREVER.
IT'S GOING TO START SOON, AND
THE PRESIDENT WILL INDICATE HOW
SOON.
HOW DO YOU THINK THAT'S GOING TO
GO?
>> LOOK, IT'S GOING TO BE
CONTROVERSIAL, BUT I THINK IT
NEEDS TO BE DONE.
IT'S NOT A QUESTION SHOULD IT BE
DONE, IT HAS TO BE DONE.
AS YOU SAID, NEIL, I DID THIS
WHEN I WAS THE EXECUTIVE
ASSOCIATE DIRECTOR AT ICE.
I RAN A0■■■■■óstvós■v■  N■v<n<■M
?C?E?E?E■E■E■E■E■g■I■E?C?C■@■@■E
DUE■@■@ç■ p/■■(■■■■iDíf■■N■Nó■,
THERE'S NO CONSEQUENCE WHO CAN
COME IN LEGALLY.
NEIL: WHAT DO YOU DO WITH
SANCTUARY CITIES, TOWNS OR
STATES?
THEY'RE GOING TO DO EVERYTHING
TO MAKE SURE THAT THE FEDS CAN'T
GET IN THERE.
>> WELL, THEY'RE NOT GOING TO
STOP THE FEDS FROM DOING THEIR
JOBS.
THEY CANNOT ASSIST, OR THEY CAN
DO WHAT THE OAKLAND MAYOR DID
AND GIVE THEM A HEADS-UP, ICE IS
IN TOWN.
NEIL: THAT'S ILLEGAL, THE
HEADS-UP IS AN ILLEGAL ACT,
RIGHT?
>> KNOW THE ONLY THAT, BUT YOU
HAD A CONGRESSMAN THE OTHER DAY,
OCASIO-CORTEZ TALKING ABOUT
PEOPLE TAKING THEM INTO THEIR
HOMES.
AND ICE -- THESE PEOPLE HAD DUE
PROCESS THROUGH TAXPAYER EXPENSE
AND ORDERED BOO  BY A JUDGE TO
GO HOME AND IF YOU AND I IGNORED
AN ORDER, WHAT WOULD HAPPEN?
IF THIS DOESN'T HAPPEN, THEY
MIGHT AS WELL OPEN IT UP,
BECAUSE WE HAVE NO SOVEREIGNTY.
IF PEOPLE WANT TO STEP IN THE
WAY OF ICE, LOOK FURTHER.
IT'S A CRIME TO IMPEDE FEDERAL
LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICER.
NEIL: THE LAW IS ON YOUR SIDE,
NO DOUBT ABOUT THAT, IMAGES CAN
PLAY HAVOC IN THE MIDDLE OF THIS
AND THE REASON I'M THINKING, I'M
HOLD ENOUGH TO REMEMBER THE
ELIAN GONZALEZ CASE WHEN HE WAS
SEIZED FROM A HOME AND
ULTIMATELY SENT BACK TO CUBA AND
IT WAS THOSE IMAGES, LEGAL AS
THEY WERE, TO RETRIEVE HIM, THAT
STUCK IN AMERICAN'S HEADS DURING
THE CLINTON ADMINISTRATION.
THAT'S GOING TO BE INEVITABLE,
THE IMAGE OF ICE AGENTS, RAMMING
ON DOORS TRYING TO GET PEOPLE,
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE ARRESTED, YOU
HAVE TO GO BACK.
HOW IS THAT ALL GOING TO GO
DOWN?
>> LOOK, I THINK FOR THOSE
PEOPLE WHO WANT TO PUSH THAT
MESSAGE, I THINK YOU NEED TO ASK
ONE QUESTION, WHAT IS YOUR
OPTION?
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
BECAUSE IF THERE'S NO INTEGRITY
IN THE SYSTEM, IF PEOPLE CAN
MESSAGE?;?;■■■■■■■á■■■■>■>■>■>■
■■ HERE■y■1■1■7■7■7■7■7■7■7■7■77
■7■7■7■7■7■7■7■7■7■>■7■>■7■gCE■
FEDERAL JUDGE■p■■■p■p■■■p■p■p■XE
LAW, IT'S SAVING LIFE.
31% OF WOMEN ARE RAPED, CHILDREN
ARE DYING.
WE'VE GOT TO SEND THE MESSAGE
IT'S NOT OKAY.
CRIMINAL ORGANIZATIONS ARE
SMUGGLING THE PEOPLE.
IT'S ABOUT SAVING LIVES AND
TAKING MONEY OUT OF CRIMINAL
ORGANIZATIONS HANDS.
AND AS SAD AS ENFORCING THE LAW
IS, IT DOESN'T MEAN WE IGNORE
IT.
NEIL: AND I'D BE REMISS IF I
DIDN'T MENTION THE FACEBOOK
POSTINGS OF THE PRESIDENT, AND
WORKERS, WHO IT DISPARAGING
COMMENTS THEY MADE ABOUT THOSE
WHO THEY WERE PROTECTING AT
THESE FACILITIES OR THOSE WHO
VISITED THEM.
DO YOU BELIEVE IF IT'S PROVEN
THAT MANY OF THEM SAID THE
THINGS THEY ALLEGED TO HAVE
SAID, THAT THEY SHOULD BE
TERMINATED?
>> I'LL WAIT TO SEE WHAT THE
INVESTIGATION SHOWS.
FROM MY SOURCES, ONLY SEVERAL
PEOPLE THAT POSTED THINGS TO
THAT EXTREME, AND OF COURSE,
THEY NEED TO BE DEALT WITH.
THAT'S NOT THE WAY, THAT'S NOT
THE BORDER PATROL I KNOW AND I
THINK IT DETRACTS FROM THE FINE
WORK THAT BORDER PATROL ARE
DOING.
AT WHAT POINT WHEN YOU GO TO
WORK EVERY DAY YOU'RE CALLED A
NAZI, A RACIST AND MAKING WOMEN
DRINK OUT OF TOILETS, WHICH IS
TOTAL CRAP, AND WHEN YOU GO TO
WORK EVERY DAY AND HEAR THESE
THINGS EVERY DAY AND WHAT POINT
DOES YOUR SPIRIT GET BROKEN AND
DO THINGS YOU PROBABLY SHOULDN'T
HAVE DONE.
I'M NOT MAKING EXCUSE, THE MEN
AND WOMEN OF BORDER PATROL ARE
DOING A GOOD JOB AND THE VAST
MAJORITY OF THEM ARE DOING THIS
FOR THEIR NATION--
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
TO SHOW THIS IS A WORLDWIDE
PROBLEM, THOSE WHO TRIED TO FLEE
TO SAFER SHORES, A BOAT WITH 40
MIGRANTS ABOARD DOCKED AGAINST
AN EXPLICIT BAN ON REFUGEES.
IN ISN'T JUST IN THIS COUNTRY,
FOLKS.
THIS IS WORLDWIDE.
MORE AFTER THIS.
■Eis no catch.
Yeah the only catch
is I'm never leaving.
No I'm serious,
I live here now.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
We're the Tenney's
and we're USAA members for life.
Call USAA to start saving
on insurance today.
>>  THEY'RE GOING TO COME AFTER
YOU.
>> SURE, THEY'RE GOING TO COME
OFF ME.
>> WERE YOU PREPARED FOR THEM TO
COME AFTER YOU?
>> I WAS PREPARED FOR THEM
COMING AFTER ME.
BUT I WASN'T PREPARED FOR THE
PERSON COMING AFTER ME THE WAY
SHE DID.
NEIL: AND JOE BIDEN TALKING
ABOUT THE DEBATE PERFORMANCE AND
KAMALA HARRIS GOING TOO FAR BACK
TO A BUSING ISSUE IN THE 1970'S.
HIS CRITICS ARE QUESTIONING, IF
HE WASN'T PREPARED FOR THAT, IS
HE PREPARED FOR THE PRESIDENCY
AT ALL.
AND SO, LAUREN, LET ME ASK YOU,
IT JUST SEEMS LIKE A LOT OF
EXCUSE MAKING.
>> LOOK, I THINK YOU KNOW, YOU
ASKED TWO QUESTIONS, IS HE
PREPARED TO BE PRESIDENT?
HE CERTAINLY IS INCREDIBLY
QUALIFIED, BUT THAT'S NOT HOW
YOU GET TO BE PRESIDENT.
THE FACT IS THERE ARE 25
CANDIDATES WHO ARE COMING AFTER
HIM SITTING AT THE TOP OF THE
POLLS, IT'S NOT A GREAT PLACE TO
BE EARLY ON, BECAUSE IT OPENS UP
A MILLION DOORS TO SCRUTINIZE
EVERY PIECE OF HIS RECORDS.
YOUNGER VOTERS ARE PAYING CLOSE
ATTENTION, YOUNGER VOTERS AND
WOMEN.
NEIL: HAS HE LOST THEM?
>> NO HE HASN'T LOST THEM.
BUT HE'LL HAVE A SERIOUS PROBLEM
IF HE DOESN'T TURN IT AROUND.
AND KAMALA HARRIS AND OTHERS ARE
OPENING UP, FOR MINORITY VOTERS,
WOMEN VOTERS, HE'S POLLING WELL
IN SOUTH CAROLINA, BUT I THINK
SHE WANTS TO CHIP AWAY AT THAT
AND THAT'S EXACTLY WHY SHE WENT
AFTER HIM ONA PARTICULAR
ISSUE.
NEIL: JOSEPH, IIGHT HAVE
MISSED THIS, THE PRESIDENT
HASN'T MADE MUCH ABOUT KAMALA
HARRIS, NORMALLY IT COULD MEAN
HE'S WORRIED, OR HOPING THAT JOE
BIDEN HAS RIGHTED THE SHIP
BECAUSE HE HAS THE MONIKERS,
SLEEPY JOE AND--
>> JOE BIDEN CAUSEf%■IlI■I■I■%■
THREAT TO HIS REELECTION.
■■■■■■■■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@F@F@T
HIS RECORD NOT THAT I'M GIVING
HIM ADVICE, LOOK FOR THE RECORD,
BUSING DIDN'T WORK.
WE'VE GOT SCHOOLS MORE
SEGREGATED THAN JIM CSOUTH.
THIS WOMAN WHO IS A SENATOR WHO
I HAVE RESPECT FOR CAME OUT WITH
AN ATTACK ON AN ISSUE SHE
BASICALLY AGREED WITH ME ON FOR
THE PURPOSE OF SELLING T-SHIRTS.
>> AND JUST NOT TO BE ARED--
>> WHETHER YOU PAL AROUND WITH
SEGREGATIONISTS, BUT THE BUS
THING.
>> WHAT WAS HE DOING?
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,■■ ■í■í■í■
EN THERE MORE
LATELY, ORE DEBATE HE
WASN'T MAKING PUBLIC
APPEARANCES, HE WASN'T PREPAREDí
I DON'T KNOW IF HE WAS WATCHING
CAT VIDEOS ON THE INTERNET,   ■
CANDY CRUSH, I DON'T KNOW.
NEIL: WOULDN'T&; BE COOL IF
HE WAS UP THERE AND ACTUALLY
ING CANDY CRUSH.
>> MAYBE HE'S ADDICT TODAY CANDY
CRUSH AND THAT'S WHY HE÷ú■ID
POORLY, I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I WOULD THINK IF YOU WERE IN
FRONT OF MILLIONS OF PEOPLE,
YOU'D DO YOUR ■■
>> IN FAIRNESS, HE HAS A
LIFETIME OF EXPERIENCE.  HE
ADMITTED HE WASN'T.
>> HE CLEARLY HAD A BAD NIGHT.
THE REALITY IT'S INCREDIBLY TO
SIT ON TOP OF THE POLL WHEN
YOU'VE GOT 24 PEOPLE CHASING
YOU.
NEIL: LOOK AT JED BUSH AT THE
TOP OF THE POLLS.
>> AND THIS EARLY.
>> AND HAD THAT MOMENT.
THAT'S NOT A GREAT PLACE TO BE
AND I'VE SAID FROM THE
BEGINNING, I THINK HIS NUMBERS
ARE GOING TO CONTINUE TO FALL
BEFORE THEY COME BACK UP.
DEMOCRATS HAVE AN ENORMOUS FIELD
OF CHOICES AND ISSUES TO
EXPLORE.
THERE'S A WHOLE NEW GENERATION
OF VOTERS WHO DON'T HAVE THE
HISTORY WITH HIM.
NEIL: THEY DON'T KNOW IT AND
LIKE A PASSING SHIP IN THE
NIGHT.
>> THEY DON'T.
>> THEY'RE GOING TO BE KEY--
>> THE KEY TO THIS ELECTION IS
NOT JUST ABOUT THE PRIMARY VOTE.
WHAT'S GOING TO TURN 2020 FOR
THE DEMOCRATS IS GOING TO BE
ENTHUSIASM AND ENERGY OF NEW
VOTERS.
GEN Z, AND GEN Y.
WOMEN AND PEOPLE--
>> LET ME ASK WHERE THEARTY
LIES AND JOE BIDEN WAS SAYING
ALEXANDRIA OCASIO-CORTEZ, I'LL
ASK YOU ABOUT THIS, JOE, SHE'S
BRIGHT AND BRILLIANT, BUT TOO
FAR LEFT.
IN OTHER WORDS, SAYING OUR GAINS
HAVE COME FROM MORE MODERATE
VICTORIES.
AND HE'S RIGHT OF THE 40, I
GUESS ELECTED TO THE HOUSE, I
THINK 32 FIT THE MODERATE LABEL.
THAT MIGHT BE
OVERGENERALLYLIZING IT AND NOT
THE OCASIO-CORTEZ LABEL.
SO SAYING THAT DID HE KIND OF
BURY HIMSELF?
>> I THINK HE'S SPEAKING THE
TRUTH.
HAVING SAID THAT MIGHT GIVE HIM
TREPIDATIONS AND DIFFICULTIES
GETTING THROUGH THE PROCESS.
THE ONLY PEOPLE TALKING ABOUT
THIS DEMOCRATIC PARTY EXPANDING
LEFT ARE PEOPLE WHO LIVE IN
DISTRICTS THAT THEY COULD LOSE
EVEN IF THEY'RE RUNNING
AGAINST--
>> YOU'RE ARGUING THAT HE IS--
WHEN HE SAYS HE'S WORRIED ABOUT
THE PARTY MOVING TOO, TOO FAR
LEFT, PROMISING MEDICARE FOR
ALL, COLLEGE DEBT, RIGHTS FOR
ILLEGALS AND THAT THAT ISN'T IN
SYNC WITH HIS DEMOCRATIC--
BASICALLY ON THE PULSE OF THE
PARTY MORE SO THAN AOC IS
TALKING ABOUT--
■I ABOUT THA
BECAUSE LOOK AT AT THE DEBATES
HE LOST SO SUPPORT AND ELIZABETH
WARREN GAINED SUPPORT AND SHE'S
VERY PROGRESSIVE.
AND PRIMARY VOTERS TEPID TO BE
MORE PROGRESSIVE THAN PEOPLE IN
GENERAL ELECTIONS.
NEIL: THE REPUBLICAN VOTERS TEND
TO BE MORE CONSERVATIVE.
>> TRYING TO RUN A GENERAL
ELECTION DURING A PRIMARY.
NEIL: AND HE HASN'T WON IT YET.
>> HE HASN'T WON IT AND HE TRIED
TO EQUIVOCATE ON THAT DURING THE
CNN INTERVIEW THAT HE DOESN'T
WANT TO BE PRESUMPTUOUS.
NEIL: YOU WANT THE DEMOCRAT TO
WIN, AND COULD YOU BE WORRIED
ABOUT THINGS THAT PROMISES
PROPOSAL THAT EVEN THE
DEMOCRATIC VOTER IN THE COUNTRY
DOESN'T--
>> I DON'T.
WHAT IS THE POINT OF THE PRIMARY
IN A PRIMARY LIKE THIS?
IT'S A BATTLE OF IDEAS, FAR TO
THE LEFT, SOMEWHERE IN THE
MIDDLE AND LAND SOMEWHERE MORE
IN LINE WITH THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE, BUT I THINK IT'S A
VALUABLE PROCESS, THAT'S WHY I
DON'T AGREE WITH A LOT OF PEOPLE
ON THE LEFT WHO SAY WE NEED TO
KULL THE FIELD SO QUICKLY.
THERE'S A BENEFIT TO THE DUNT
WHEN YOU'VE GOT QUALIFIED PEOPLE
DEBATING IDEAS ON THE COUNTRY.
AND I THINK IT'S BACK TO THE
CENTER AS WE'RE CLOSER TO THE
NOMINATION, BUT HE'S WRONG TO
HOLD THIS--
HE'S GOING TO ALIENATE A LOT OF
THE PEOPLE THAT HE REALLY NEEDS
TO TURN OUT FOR HIM.
>> I DISAGREE.
I THINK YET AGAIN, JOE BIDEN IS
PLAYING A GAME RIGHT NOW HE
BELIEVES HE'S GOING TO DEPEND ON
RELIABLE VOTERS.
RELIABLE VOTERS ARE OLDER
VOTERS.
OLDER BLACK VOTERS, AND THOSE
ARE THE PEOPLE HE'S TALKING
ABOUT.
HE FELL BECAUSE HE DIDN'T DO A
GOODB, HE KIND OF SUCKS,
BUT--
>> MAYBE HE'S A LOUSY CANDIDATE.
>> WHEN YOU LOOK AT ELIZABETH
WARREN RISING, RISING NOT ON THE
STRENGTHS OF JOE BIDEN, BUT
PEOPLE BELIEVE SHE'S THE
ORIGINAL PERSON WITH THE
TRILLION DOLLAR GIVEAWAYS, THE
PLANS TO BERNIE'S RHETORIC.
AND YOU SEE KAMALA HARRIS GOING
AFTER JOE BIDEN HER PATH GOES
DIRECTLY ON JOE BIDEN.
NEIL: THAT'S AT THE TOP.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE ON A
HOT SATURDAY.
WE APPRECIATE THAT.
AND MANY OF YOU ARE OLD ENOUGH
WHEN FRANKLIN ROOSEVELT WAS
TRYING TO PACK THE SUPREME
COURT?
IS THIS PRESIDENT TRYING TO DO
THE SAME WITH THE FEDERAL
WE CONNECT, YOU DECIDE.
■@■@
♪ When you have nausea,
heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, upset stomach,
diarrhea ♪
Try New Pepto Liquicaps for fast
relief and ultra-coating.
♪ Nausea, heartburn,
indigestion, upset stomach,
diarrhea ♪
Get powerful relief with new
Pepto Bismol Liquicaps.
This is the couple who
wanted to get away
who used Expedia to book
the vacation rental
that led to the ride
♪
which took them
to the place
where they discovered
that sometimes
a little down time
can lift you right up.
♪
Flights, hotels, cars,
activities, vacation rentals.
Expedia.
Everything you need to go.
>>  ALL RIGHT, I DON'T THINK THE
PRESIDENT IS STILL A FAN OF THE
FEDERAL RESERVE BLASTING IT IN
TWEETS, IN PART STRONG JOBS
REPORT AND LOW INFLATION AND
OTHER COUNTRIES AROUND THE WORLD
DOING EVERYTHING POSSIBLE TO
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THE UNITED
STATES KNOWING OUR FEDERAL
RESERVE DOESN'T HAVE A CLUE,
RAISED RATES TOO SOON, TOO
OFTEN.
AND RUBBING MORE SALT IN THE
WOUND, THE MOST DIFFICULT
PROBLEM IS NOT OUR COMPETITORS,
IT'S THE FEDERAL RESERVE.
JOINING ME THE FORMER FED
NOMINEE, STEVE MOORE.
HE WILL NOT LET GO OF THIS.
IS THAT HURTING HIM?
WHAT DO YOU THINK.
LET ME START BY SAYING THIS WHEN
I WAS DRIVING IN, NEIL, I THINK
YOU AND I ARE ABOUT THE SAME
AGE.
THIS MAY HAVE BEEN THE BEST
ECONOMY WE'VE SEEN IN OUR
LIFETIME.
WHEN YOU'VE GOT THE LOWEST
UNEMPLOYMENT RATE IN 50 YEARS,
NO INFLATION, RISING WAGES,
YOU'VE GOT 7 1/2 MILLION MORE
JOBS THAN PEOPLE TO FILL THEM.
THE STOCK MARKET IS NOW
OFFICIALLY UP 50% SINCE DONALD
TRUMP WAS ELECTED.
NEIL: HE'S BLAMING FED THAT IT
COULD BE A LOT HIGHER.
I HAD NO IDEA WERE YOU 39.
[LAUGHTER].
>> YOU'RE YOUNGER THAN I AM BUT,
NO, THE REASON I SAY THAT, NE
TO YOUR TION, ISN'TT ABOUT
TIME■ ■ ■ ■  THIS
I REMEMBER DURING ■@■@
WORKING FOR TRUMP AND PEOPLE
AVE THE SECOND GRADE■@■ E■÷■÷
DEPRES
AND NOW WE HA■@ THE BEST ECONOMY
IN YEARS.
HE'S FRUSTRATEDE FED AND
THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS HE
NOMINATED ME.
I THINK THE FED IS TOO TIGHT AS
WELL.
NEIL: NOW HE'S NAMING TWO
PEOPLE, THE INTERPRETATION IS
THAT THEY'LL DO HIS BIDDING,
THAT THEY AGREE WITH HIM.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> THEY SHARE HIS VISION OF THE
ECONOMY.
THE PROBLEM WITH THE FED AND
THIS HAS BEEN A PROBLEM NOT
RECENTLY, BUT FOR 30 YEARS.
THE FED BELIEVES IF YOU GET TOO
MUCH INFLATION I MEAN, TOO MANY
PEOPLE WORKING, TOO MUCH GROWTH,
WAGES RISING SOMEHOW THEY HAVE
TO SNUFF THAT OUT.
AND DONALD TRUMP THE FIRST TIME
I MET HIM WE ARE GOING TO GET
THIS ECONOMY MOVING 3 TO 4% UP A
YEAR FROM OBAMA.
AND EVERY TIME WE GET A GOOD
JOBS REPORT OR THE GROWTH COMES
UP OR WAGES RISE THE FED WANTS
TO, YOU KNOW, PULL IT BACK.
AND I THINK THAT'S WRONG-HEADED.
WE CAN GROW THIS ECONOMY WITHOUT
INFLATION FASTER AND TRUMP IS
RIGHT ABOUT THIS.
NEIL: ARE YOU WORRIED--
I GET WHERE YOU'RE COMING AND
THE PRESIDENT IS COMING AND HE'S
PROVEN RIGHT BECAUSE THEY DID GO
TO 4.
>> EXACTLY RIGHT.
NEIL: HAVING SAID THAT, DOES HE
RECOGNIZE HOW WEIRD IT SOUNDS TO
LOVE A ROBUST ECONOMY AND A
STRONG JOBS AND STILL ADVOCATES
FOR LOWER RATES?
IT'S LIKES AN OXYMORON.
>> NO, IT ISN'T.
WE THINK THE ECONOMY CAN GROW
FASTER.
WE'RE ONLY GOING TO GET 2%.
THE ECONOMY SHOULD BE GROWING 3
TO 4.
BY THE WAY IF HE GETS THE TRADE
DEAL WITH CHINA AND THE FED RATE
CUT IN JULY I THINK YOU'RE
LOOKING AT--
IF YOU THINK THE ECONOMY IS
STRONG, BUT, WAIT UNTIL THAT
HAPPENS.
WE HAVE A DIFFERENT MODEL IN
MIND.
WE THINK THE CAPACITY OF THE
U.S. ECONOMY TO GROW FASTER FOR
MORE JOBS TO BE CREATED, MORE
PEOPLE IN THE WORK FORCE IS A
LOT FASTER.
REMEMBER, LARRY SUMMERS, WHO WAS
BILL CLINTON AND BARACK OBAMA'S
ECONOMIST, YOU KNOW, BEFORE THE
ELECTION SAID THE TOP MOST
GROWTH WE CAN GET IN THIS
COUNTRY IS 2%.
REMEMBER THAT.
NEIL: YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> NO, WE'RE THROWING THIS MODEL
OUT.
WE'LL GROW THIS ECONOMY FASTER
AND LOW INFLATION, LOW
UNEMPLOYMENT AND HOW ABOUT THAT,
50% INCREASE IN THE STOCK
MARKET, THAT'S 10 TRILLION--
>> GREAT WISDOM FOR A
39-YEAR-OLD MAN.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
[LAUGHTER]
>>  HAVE A GREAT WEEKENDS.
STEVE MOORE.
AFTER THIS, ASK THIS QUESTION,
MILLENNIALS LEAVING CITIES, SO
FINANCIALLY TIGHT, THAT THEY
CAN'T MAKE IT IN THE BIG CITY.
WHAT IS THAT SAYING?
AFTER THIS.
y hepatitis C,
I felt I couldn't be at my best
for my family.
In only 8 weeks with MAVYRET,
I was cured and left those
doubts behind.
I faced reminders of my hep C
every day.
But in only 8 weeks
with MAVYRET,