shattering lineup.
Pay no interest for 72 months
on most Buick models.
Captioning made possible
by Johnson & Johnson,
committed to improving health
for everyone, everywhere.
♪ ♪ ♪
>> Pauley: GOOD MORNING.
I'M JANE PAULEY, AND THIS IS
"SUNDAY MORNING."
OSCAR SUNDAY MORNING AND IN
HONOR OF THE OCCASION WE ARE OFF
TO MOVIES.
WE WILL BEGIN WHERE ANNIE BEGINS
AND WE WILL FIGURE OUT HOW 0 TO
BREAK INTO THE BUSINESS.
TRACY SMITH WILL SHOW US HOW
IT'S DONE.
>> TWO OPTIONS.
YOU EITHER FOLLOW MY RULES, OR
FOLLOW MY RULES, CAPICE?
>> THANK YOU.
>> OH.
>> THANKS.
>> I CAN DO IT A DIFFERENT WAY.
>> NO, THAT'S FINE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> OKAY, IT'S ONLY A MOVIE.
BUT REAL-LIFE HOLLYWOOD CASTING
IS DEFINITELY NOT FOR THE FAINT
OF HEART.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, I'LL SEE YOU ON THE ROAD,
GUYS.
>> WHAT WOULD YOU SAY IS THE
TOUGHEST PART OF THE CASTING
PROCESS?
>> TELLING SOMEONE THAT THEY
DIDN'T GET A JOB.
>> LATER ON "SUNDAY
MORNING"--CHASING A HOLLYWOOD
DREAM.
>ANGIE DICKERSON FOUND STARDOMM.
TODAY SHE LOOKING BACK WITH OUR
MO ROCCA.
>> FEW STARS EVER HAD ANGIE
DICKERSON'S POTENT MIX OF
TALENT, LOOKS AND SMARTS.
>> HOW IS A DAY IN YOUR LIFE
NOW?
>> I GET UP.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING?
YOU KNOW HOW OLD I AM.
I AM NOT GOING TO BE DATING SOME
YOUNG GUY.
UNLESS HE CALLS FIRST.
>> ANGIE DICKERSON LAYING HER
CARDS ON THE TABLE, AHEAD ON
SUNDAY MORNING.
>> 0 SOME NIEWFS ARE ALL ABOUT
THE SET.
THE SHE SHOWS US BEFORE AND
AFTER.
LIGHTING THE EVERYTHING.
LIGHTING CREATES THE MOOD, IT
CREATES THE WARMTH.
>> TODAY MEREDITH BAER USES HER
MAGIC TO MAKE OVER HOMES FOR
SALE.
>> THIS IS BEFORE ♪
>> AND THIS IS AFTER.
>> A 24-HOUR TRANSFORMATION.
LATER ON SUNDAY MORNING.
>> FROM THERE IT IS ON TO A
STATION BREAK.
AT A CHAIN OF RAILROAD REST
STOPS PAID FAMOUS BY AN
OSCAR-WINNING SONG.
>> MICHELLE MILLER HAS JUST THE
TICKET.
♪ BACK IN OHIO OF.
THE OSCAR FOR BEST ORIGINAL SONG
IN 1946 WENT TO THIS JOHNNY
MERCER CLASSIC ♪
♪ ON THE SANTA FE, TOPEKA AND
THE SANTA FE ♪
>> MEMORIALIZED BY JUDY GARLAND
IN THE HARVEY GIRLS.
>> IT'S BASED ON A TRUE STORY.
>> THEY HAD BRAVERY TO LEAVE
THEIR SMALL TOWNS, AND TO TRAVEL
ON THE TRAIN, THESE WERE UNIQUE
WOMEN.
>> ALL AGOOD, ALL ABOARD, AHEAD
ON SUNDAY MORNING.
>> LEE COWAN HAS SOME AMAZING
FACE FACTS, PLUS STEVE HARTMAN,
JIM GAFFIGAN AND THE OSCAR
PICKS.
>> FIRST THE HEADLINES FOR
SUNDAY MORNING.
FEBRUARY 24TH, 2019.
>> POPE FRANCIS TODAY CLOSED A
VATICAN SUMMIT ON THE CATHOLIC
CHURCH'S STAKES ABUSE SCANDAL.
YESTERDAY, A CARDINAL ADMITTED
THE CHURCH DESTROYED DECADES OF
FILES DOCUMENTING VICTIMS'
CLAIMS.
A BOEING 767 CARGO JETLINER
CRASHED INTO A BAY EAST OF
HOUSTON YESTERDAY, KILLING ALL
THREE CREW MEMBERS.
WITNESSES SAY THE ENGINE'S
SURGED BEFORE THE JET STRUCK THE
WATER NOSE FIRST.
R. KELLY REMAINS JAILED IN
CHICAGO.
THE GRAMMY AWARD-WINNING SINGER
IS CHARGED WITH SEXUAL ABUSE
INVOLVING FOUR FEMALE VICTIMS;
THREE WERE MINORS.
AS FOR PATRIOTS OWNER ROBERT
KRAFT, CHARGED IN A SEX CASE,
REPORTS SAY HE ATTENDED MEDIA
MOGUL BARRY DILLER'S OSCARS
PARTY IN CALIFORNIA YESTERDAY.
THEN THERE IS THE WEATHER.
THERE'S MAJOR FLOODING IN THE
DEEP SOUTH AFTER RECORD RAINS.
IN MISSISSIPPI, TORNADOES PROVED
DESTRUCTIVE.
BLIZZARDS ARE BLOWING THROUGH
THE MIDWEST.
IT IS ALL PART OF A SEVERE
WEATHER SYSTEM PUSHING ACROSS
THE EAST N THE WEST THERE IS
SNOW FROM WASHINGTON TO WYOMING.
FOR WEEK AHEAD, IT IS WINTER, IT
IS SPRING, AND SPRING IS ONLY 28
DAYS AWAY.
>>
YOU SAY YOU WANT TO BE IN
PICTURES?
THAT TIMELESS EXPRESSION
CAPTURES THE LONGING OF COUNT
LESS YOUNG ACTORS IN SEARCH OF
THEIR FIRST BIG BREAK.
>> OUR COVER STORY IS FROM TRACY
SMITH.
>> IN HOLLYWOOD, IT SEEMS, YOU
NEVER KNOW WHEN THE NEXT OSCAR
WINNER MIGHT SHOW UP.
>> ♪
♪ OF COURSE MARILYN MONROE NEVER
TOOK HOE AN ACADEMY AWARD, BUT
IF YOU CAN TAKE YOUR EYES OFF OF
HER FOR A SECOND.
>> YOU CAN SPOT SOMEONE ELSE IN
THIS SCENE.
YOU DID.
>> GEORGE
GEORGE CHAKIRIS WAS A DANCER--A
KID FROM OHIO WHO BASICALLY USED
HIS FEET TO BREAK INTO THE
MOVIES--INCLUDING THIS SPOT IN
MARILYN'S CHORUS LINE.
>> DIAMONDS ARE A GIRL'S BEST
FRIEND? I WAS ONE OF THE GUYS IN
IT, YEAH.
>> AND DID YOU HAVE INTERACTION
WITH MARILYN?
>> NO, SHE WAS VERY QUIET.
[MUSIC]
>> AND WHEN MOVIE MUSICALS
THEMSELVES WENT QUIET A FEW
YEARS LATER, CHAKIRIS FOUND WORK
WITH THE LONDON CAST OF A HIT
BROADWAY SHOW-"WEST SIDE STORY."
AND THEN THE RUMORS STARTED
FLYING ABOUT A FILM VERSION.
>> I REMEMBER ONE OF THE THINGS
WE HEARD WAS THAT-- THAT PEOPLE
BEING CONSIDERED FOR THE MOVIE
WERE ELIZABETH TAYLOR AND ELVIS
PRESLEY.
SO WE THOUGHT, "OKAY, THEY'RE
USING BIG STARS AND--"
BUT-- BUT ONE DAY, FIVE-- FIVE
OF US GOT LETTERS FROM UNITED
ARTISTS ASKING US TO DO TESTS.
>> TO DO A SCREEN TEST?
>> YEAH. IT WAS A FANTASTIC DAY,
YOU KNOW, WE WERE DOING OUR
TESTS WITH A CAMERA AND A
DIRECTOR.
I MEAN, IT WAS JUST, YOU KNOW,
WOW.
>> IT WAS "WOW" ALL RIGHT:
AFTER HIS SCREEN TEST, CHAKIRIS
WAS CAST AS THE PUERTO RICAN
GANG LEADER BERNARDO--ACTING AND
DANCING IN SOME OF THE MOST
SPECTACULAR AND STRENUOUS SCENES
EVER FILMED.
COULD YOU FEEL YOURSELF GIVING
IT YOUR ALL?
I MEAN, HOW TAXING WAS IT?
IT NEVER FELT TAXING.
IT JUST FELT GOOD.
>> GOOD ENOUGH, WE NOW KNOW, FOR
AN ACADEMY AWARD, ALONGSIDE
CO-STAR RITA MORENO.
>> AN AMAZING EVENING.
JUST AN AMAZING EVENING. WE HAD
SO MUCH FUN.
>> BUT IF THE OSCARS ARE THE TOP
OF THE MOUNTAIN, YOU MIGHT SAY
THESE ARE THE FOOTHILLS:
THE CASTING OFFICES--LIKE
EXCLUSIVE STUDIOS ON SUNSET
BOULEVARD---ARE OFTEN A WOULD-BE
MOVIE STAR'S FIRST STOP.
>> SABRINA!
>> CASTING DIRECTORS AMANDA
LENKER DOYLE AND CHRISSY
FIORELLI-ELLINGTON--HAVE SPENT
YEARS LOOKING FOR THAT PERFECT
FACE IN THE CROWD---AND THEY
WANT TO SEE A LOT MORE OF THOSE
FACES TODAY.
>> HI.
>> HEY.
>> BEYOND MOVIES AND BROADCAST
TV, THERE ARE STREAMING
PLATFORMS FROM NETFLIX TO
YOUTUBE ORIGINALS.
AND THEY ALL NEED ACTORS.
>> WHO DOES THAT?
>> I DO.
[APPLAUSE]
>> SO, IT SOUNDS, IN A WAY, LIKE
THE CHANCES OF BREAKING INTO
HOLLYWOOD ARE BETTER TODAY THAN
MAYBE THEY'VE EVER BEEN?
>> THEY ARE.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH. 'CAUSE THERE'S--
THERE'S JUST A LOT OF WORK.
THERE'S A LOT OF WORK AND SO
THERE'S MORE OPPORTUNITIES FOR A
LOT OF PEOPLE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> YEAH.
>> OK, COME ON IN.
>> WE SHOULD SAY THAT TV NEWS
CAMERAS ARE NOT USUALLY ALLOWED
IN AN ACTUAL CASTING SESSION.
BUT THEY AGREED TO SHOW US HOW
IT'S DONE--IN REAL TIME. AND
WITH REAL ACTORS.
>> MY NAME IS FAYNA SANCHEZ.
>> ERIC MARTIG.
>> I'M SABRINA REVELLE.
>> TOM MYERS.
>> I'VE BEEN IN LA FOR ABOUT 12
YEARS.
>> WHAT, NOW, ALMOST 20 YEARS?
>> QUITE A LONG TIME.
>> THAT'S MY DREAM, WORKING
ACTOR BUT ALSO TO EVENTUALLY
PRODUCE AND DIRECT.
HOW DO YOU PAY THE BILLS?
UH, BARTENDING.
>> AND--AS YOU'D EXPECT--THE
ASPIRING STARS SHOW UP, SIGN IN,
AND DO THEIR BEST FOR THE
CASTING DIRECTOR.
>> AND I'M HEADIN' DOWN SOUTH.
>> THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH. NOW, WILL
YOU TURN YOUR HEAD FOR US?
>> SURE.
>> IT WAS MUCH THE SAME IN
MARLON BRANDO'S DAY.
BUT BACK THEN THEY NEEDED A
WHOLE STUDIO TO SEE HOW AN ACTOR
LOOKED ON FILM.
>> LET'S GET OUTTA HERE. EVERY
TIME I COME BACK I FEEL LIKE I
GOTTA BREAK OUT.
>> AND NOW, ANY VIDEO CAMERA
WILL DO.
>> YES. I AM NOW LIVING MY
HOLLYWOOD DREAM.
>> STILL, THE PROCESS OF PUTTING
YOURSELF OUT THERE IS AS TOUGH
AS IT EVER WAS. THOUGH MAYBE NOT
QUITE AS BRUTAL AS YOU MIGHT SEE
IN THE MOVIES.
TWO OPTIONS. YOU EITHER FOLLOW
MY RULES OR FOLLOW MY RULES,
CAPICE?
THANK YOU.
OH.
THANKS.
>> I CAN DO IT A DIFFERENT WAY.
NO, THAT'S FINE. THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
WHEN YOU GUYS SAW THAT SCENE IN
"LA LA LAND," DID YOU GO, "NO!"
IT'S LIKE NOT FUNNY ANYMORE.
NO.
'CAUSE WE'RE NOT MEAN.
WE'RE REALLY NICE. AND WE WANT
TO CREATE A REALLY SAFE SPACE
FOR EVERYBODY.
>> AND THE KEY WORD NOW IS
EVERYBODY.
>> ACCORDING TO USC'S ANNENBERG
INCLUSION INITIATIVE, LEAD
CHARACTERS IN LAST YEAR'S
FEATURE FILMS WERE MORE DIVERSE
THAN EVER---WITH A LONG WAY
STILL TO GO.
>> BUT BEYOND TALENT AND
TRAINING AND A THOUSAND OTHER
THINGS, IT OFTEN COMES DOWN TO
THAT MYSTERIOUS QUALITY COMMONLY
KNOWN AS THE "IT" FACTOR.
LOOK THIS IS MY LIFE, AND IT'S A
BATTLE WITHIN, I GOTTA.ù
>> TERRENCE HOWARD HAD "IT,"
SAYS LONGTIME CASTING DIRECTOR
KIMBERLY HARDIN.
>> I DID "HUSTLE AND FLOW" WITH
HIM. AND THEN HE JUST
SKYROCKETED FROM THERE.
>> OSCAR NOMINATION HELPS.
>> YOU KNOW. YEAH.
>> SO I KNOW THE "IT" FACTOR IS
HARD TO NARROW DOWN, BUT YOU
KNOW THERE ARE PEOPLE OUT THERE
SAYING, "WELL, HOW DO I GET
THAT--"
>> GET THE-- YEAH, THE IT
FACTOR. YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS?
IT'S A COMBINATION OF BEING SURE
OF YOURSELF, I THINK. MAYBE
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
>> IT'S LIKE, A SELF-CONFIDENCE?
>> IT'S LIKE, A SELF-CONFIDENCE
WITHOUT BEING EGOTISTICAL.
>> PHONE.
>> PHONE? HE SAID PHONE?
>> AND SOMETIMES THE CASTING
CHOICE IS SO OBVIOUS IT CAN
BRING YOU TO TEARS.
>> 'MEMBER THAT KID FROM ET?
>> DID YOU KNOW WATCHING HENRY
THOMAS'S AUDITION FOR "E.T."
THAT HE WAS THE KID?
>> I ABSOLUTELY KNEW.
AND IT IS, TO THIS DAY, HANDS
DOWN, THE BEST AUDITION THAT
I'VE EVER BEEN IN.
>> VETERAN CASTING DIRECTOR
MARCI LIROFF WAS PART OF A TEAM
THAT CAST HENRY AS ELLIOTT.
>> I'M GONNA TAKE HIM.
>> THIS IS HIS SCREEN TEST FOR
DIRECTOR STEVEN SPIELBERG.
>> WELL, I'M AFRAID I HAVE TO,
SON.
>> YOU CAN'T TAKE HIM AWAY HE'S
MINE!
>> AND WHEN HENRY STARTED
CRYING, WE ALL STARTED WEEPING.
AND WE'RE S--STANDING BEHIND THE
CAMERA GOING LIKE THIS.
AND-- AND IT WAS-- SO EMOTIONAL.
>> AND HE WANTS TO STAY HERE. HE
LIKES IT HERE.
>> AND YOU CAN HEAR SPIELBERG'S
REACTION AT THE VERY END.
>> OK, KID, YOU GOT THE JOB.
>> AND THEN STEVEN SAYS, "YOU
GOT THE JOB, KID." AND IT WAS--
IT WAS OBVIOUSLY-- HE WAS
OBVIOUSLY THE PERFECT PERSON FOR
THE ROLE.
>> HOW OFTEN DOES THAT MAGIC
MOMENT HAPPEN?
>> NOT VERY OFTEN.
>> I THINK I GO BACK TO SAN
JUAN.
>> I KNOW A BOAT YOU CAN GET ON.
>> BYE-BYE.
>> NOW, "WEST SIDE STORY" IS
BEING REMADE.
AND THIS TIME, THE PRODUCERS ARE
LOOKING TO CAST LATIN ACTORS FOR
THE LATIN PARTS.
>> BACK IN THE DAY, WITH THE
ORIGINAL, IT WAS NOT ALL PUERTO
RICAN ACTORS.
>> NO.
>> YOU'RE NOT PUERTO RICAN.
>> NO, I'M GREEK.
>> STILL, GEORGE CHAKIRIS IS
GRATEFUL HE EVER GOT THE CHANCE.
>> IF YOU COULD BOIL IT DOWN,
WHAT DO YOU THINK WAS THE KEY
FOR YOU FOR BREAKING INTO
HOLLYWOOD, FOR MAKING IT IN
PICTURES?
>> WELL, I WAS LUCKY ENOUGH TO
BE IN "WEST SIDE STORY." WHO
KNOWS WHAT WOULD'VE HAPPENED,
YOU KNOW, IF -- IF THERE HAD
NEVER BEEN A "WEST SIDE STORY."
I WOULD'VE STILL BEEN TRYING TO
FULFILL MY DREAM.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN IT
WOULD'VE HAPPENED.
>> THERE YOU ARE.
>> THERE I AM.
>> AND AS CHAKIRIS WAS REMINDED
WHEN HE SAW A GROUP OF TEENAGERS
PERFORM RECENTLY, MAYBE THE REAL
"IT" FACTOR IS LUCK.
>> I WAS SPENDING A LOT OF TIME
IN LONDON, AND I WENT TO ONE OF
THE DRAMA SCHOOLS THERE, THE
GRADUATION PERFORMANCE.
THEY DID A MUSICAL CALLED
"LITTLE ME," A GREAT MUSICAL.
EVERY YOUNG PERSON IN THAT CAST
WAS SO WONDERFUL, AND I REMEMBER
THINKING TO MYSELF, "WHO IN THIS
GROUP IS GONNA GET LUCKY?"
'CAUSE YOU HAVE TO GET LUCKY
TOO.
YOU KNOW I GO 4 THE GIRL.
>> SIDE BY SIDE OR FACE TO FACE
JAMES DEAN AND PAUL NEWMAN
APPEARED TOGETHER IN THIS 1954
SCREEN TEST FOR THE MOVIE EAST
OF EDEN, DEAN WOULD GET THE
ROLE, BUT IT WAS NEWMAN WHO GOT
THE LONGEVITY.
>> AS LONG AS THERE HAVE BEEN
MOVIE, THERE HAVE BEEN SCREEN
TESTS.
HERE IS CHARLIE CHAPLAIN GIVING
ACTRESS GEORGIA HAIL A CLASSIC
TRYOUT FOR HIS FILM CITY LIGHTS.
THAT WAS IN 1929 HE.
>> SO WAS THIS TEST WITH A YOUNG
MARLENA DIETRICH.
>> ♪
♪ YOU ARE THE CREAM IN MY
COFFEE.
YOU ARE THE SOUL IN MY SOUP.
>> WATCH WHAT HAPPENS WHEN THE
PIANO PLAYER FUMBLES.
>> Pauley: NEARLY HALF A
CENTURY LATER, A THEN UNKNOWN
JOHN TRAVOLTA AUDITIONS FOR TV'S
WELCOME BACK COTTER.
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> I AM BARB I ARE ANY.
>> Pauley: HE WOULD BECOME
BARBARINO AND JOHN TRAVOLTA
WOULD BECOME A SUPERSTAR.
>> AND THAT BRINGS US TO DUSTIN
HOFFMAN.
>> HE WAS ALREADY FAMOUS WHEN HE
PUT ON A DRESS FOR THIS 1981
SCREEN TEST FOR THE MOVIE TUTSI.
>> A LITTLE TOO SHORT.
>> WELL I AM NOT EVEN WEARING
HEELS.
>> AS YOU CAN SEE HE REALLY
WANTED THE ROLE AND AS WE ALL
KNOW, HE WAS KIND OF A NATURAL.
>> TAXI!
TAXI!
>> Pauley: ALL RIGHT, ALL
RIGHT.
>> Pauley: AHEAD, A ROLE YOU
SINK YOUR TEETH INTO.
THIS PORTION OF SUNDAY MORNING
IS SPONSORED BY VIKING CRUISES.
>>
at Dell.com
♪
>> Pauley: ONE HOLLYWOOD ART
FORM IS ALL ABOUT FACE.
MUCH TO THE BENEFIT OF STARS
LIKE RAMI MALEK.
IN THE RUNNING TONIGHT FOR BEST
ACTOR.
A STAND-OUT PERFORMANCE, LEE
COWAN TELLS US.
WITH STAND-OUT TEETH.
♪ SOMEBODY TO LOVE ♪
>> IT SEEMS TRITE, GIVEN HIS
EXTRAORDINARY MUSICAL TALENT, TO
FOCUS ON FREDDIE MERCURY'S TEETH
- BUT IF YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE A
MOVIE ABOUT QUEEN'S LEGENDARY
FRONTMAN - THAT OVERBITE - CAN'T
BE UNDERESTIMATED.
>> I WAS BORN WITH 4 ADDITIONAL
INCISORS, MORE SPACE IN MY MOUTH
MEANS MORE RANGE.
>> ON THE RED CARPET - ACTOR
RAMI MALEK LOOKS NOTHING LIKE
MERCURY - BUT HIS PORTRAYAL IN
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY" IS SO
SPOT-ON - IT'S ALREADY EARNED
HIM A GOLDEN GLOBE, A SAG AND A
BAFTA.
AT TIMES IT'S HARD TO TELL THEM
APART - THAT'S MALEK ON THE LEFT
- THAT'S THE REAL FREDDIE
MERCURY ON THE RIGHT - A LOOK
MALEK ADMITS - WOULDN'T HAVE
WORKED WITHOUT THE MAN BEHIND
THAT MOUTH.
>> IT'S THE BIGGEST TOOTH MOVIE
I'VE EVER WORKED ON.
[LAUGHTER]
>> HIS NAME IS CHRIS LYONS - A
DENTAL TECHNICIAN BY TRADE.
I THINK WE SHOULD INCREASE THE
--
>> HE DOES REAL DENTAL WORK FOR
REAL PEOPLE AT HIS OFFICES
OUTSIDE LONDON.
[DRILL NOISE.]
>> BUT HE HAS A SIDE BUSINESS -
CALLED FANGS FX.
>> THEY'RE FROM "THE WOLFMAN."
>> OF COURSE THEY ARE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> HE'S HELPED MONSTERS -- AND
THOSE MONSTROUSLY FAMOUS --
HE GAVE MERYL STREEP A SET OF
MARGARET THATCHER TEETH.
>> AND TAKE PRIDE IN BEING
BRITISH.
[APPLAUSE]
>> YOU KILL HIM AND LET ME LIVE.
>> TILDA SWINTON GOT A MOUTHFUL
OF HIS WORK TOO.
>> THANK YOU ALL.
>> AND HE HELPED JOHN LITHGOW
GET THOSE WINSTON CHURCHILL-LIKE
JOWLS.
>> HE CREATED THESE TWO LITTLE
BLOBS THAT CLICKED ONTO MY BACK
TEETH THAT JUST SWELLED MY FACE,
BUT ALSO CHANGED MY, MY DICTION.
>> YEAH. YEAH, YEAH.
>> BUT WHEN ASKED TO RE-CREATE
FREDDIE MERCURY'S TEETH -
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
>> LYONS WORRIED HE MAY HAVE
BITTEN OFF MORE THAN HE COULD
CHEW.
>> WHEN THE OFFER FIRST CAME TO
YOU, IT'S PRETTY DAUNTING, IN
THIS PARTICULAR CASE, OUT OF ALL
THE TEETH YOU'VE DONE, 'CAUSE
THESE ARE ALMOST LIKE A
CHARACTER.
>> IT'S AN ICONIC SET OF TEETH
FOR AN ICONIC CHARACTER FROM AN
ICONIC BAND.
>> I JUST LOVE THEM.
[LAUGHTER]
>> EVERYBODY KNOWS FREDDIE'S
TEETH, AND YES, I WAS VERY
WORRIED.
UNDER PRESSURE.
>> AS THE STORY GOES, MERCURY
DIDN'T WANT TO CHANGE HIS TEETH.
>> UNDER PRESSURE
>> BECAUSE HE FEARED IT MIGHT
CHANGE THE SOUND OF HIS VOICE.
>> FREDDIE, YOUR TEETH, WHY
DON'T YOU GET YOUR TEETH FIXED?
>> I LIVE IN BRITAIN.
I DON'T WANT TO STAND OUT.
>> ROUGHLY THE SIZE
>> LYONS STARTED OFF MAKING A
SET OF INCISORS THE SAME SIZE AS
MERCURY'S.
>> AND WHEN YOU PUT THAT IN
RAMI, IT WAS JUST TOO MUCH?
>> YEAH, IT WAS TOO LUDICROUS.
IT JUST BECAME A TOTAL
CARICATURE.
[DRILL NOISE.]
>> SO LYONS KEPT SCALING THEM
BACK.
HIS REAL TEETH END THERE, AND
THEN WE BROUGHT THEM DOWN THIS
MUCH.
>> THESE TWO ARE THE ACTUAL
TEETH RAMI WORE.
>> THE TEETH HOWEVER, WERE ONLY
THE FIRST BITE IN A
TRANSFORMATION THAT MAKE-UP
ARTIST JAN SEWELL AND PROSTHETIC
DESIGNER MARK COULIER HAD TO
FINISH.
>> WHAT CAN YOU DO?
HE DOESN'T LOOK ANYTHING LIKE
FREDDIE MERCURY, REALLY.
>> RIGHT.
>> SO YOU JUST THEN HAVE TO DIAL
ALL THAT BACK, AND THEN CHOOSE
SOMETHING THAT'S GONNA JUST
ENHANCE OR CREATE AN ESSENCE OF
MUD ON YOUR FACE, BIG DISGRACE
>> BUT CREATING THAT "ESSENCE"
OF FREDDIE MERCURY -
♪ WE WILL ROCK YOU ♪
>> WOULD ALSO INVOLVE A BIT OF A
NOSE JOB FOR MALEK.
>> SING IT!
♪ WE WILL ROCK YOU ♪
>> RAMI'S GOT AN INDENT HERE.
AND FREDDIE'S GOT, YOU KNOW.
QUITE AN AQUILINE, DOESN'T HE?
>> AN AQUILINE NOSE SHAPE ACROSS
HERE.
SO WE JUST THOUGHT, WE'LL TRY
THAT, AND SEE IF THAT WORKS, YA
KNOW.
>> IT DID.  THAT'S MALEK AGAIN
ON THE LEFT - THE REAL FREDDIE
MERCURY ON THE RIGHT.
>> OKAY, IT LOOKS GREAT.
>> MALEK'S FREDDIE-LIKE NOSE WAS
SCULPTED HERE - AT COULIER
CREATURES FX - A MACABRE PLACE
WHERE DISEMBODIED HEADS STARE
BACK AT YOU FROM ALMOST EVERY
ANGLE.
>> WE DID A FACE CAST OF RAMI,
BUT WE ALSO DID THIS 3D PRINT OF
HIS HEAD, SO WHEN WE SCULPT THE
PIECE WE KNOW IT'S GONNA FIT IN
WITH HIS EYEBROWS.
>> LOVE OF MY LIFE, CAN'T YOU
SEE
>> THEN THERE WAS THE BODY HAIR
THAT MERCURY OFTEN SHOWED OFF --
STARTING WITH THAT ULTRA-THIN
80S MUSTACHE OF HIS.
DON'T TAKE IT AWAY FROM ME
BECAUSE YOU DON'T
>> IT'S PAPER THIN.
>> AS YOU CAN SEE, IT'S FINE,
FINE, FINE.
>> AND IT'S ON A FINE LACE.
EACH HAIR IS INDIVIDUALLY
KNOTTED ON THIS EXTREMELY FINE
LACE.
>> AND DID YOU DO THE CHEST HAIR
TOO?
>> WELL, YEAH, 'CAUSE HE WAS
JUST NOT QUITE AS HAIRY AS
FREDDIE.
>> AND EVEN UNDERARM HAIR?
>> NO, THAT'S ALL HIS.
HE CAN TAKE CREDIT FOR ALL OF
THAT!
>> WHEN THE FINAL LOOK ALL CAME
TOGETHER - THE LIKENESS WAS
ALMOST EERIE.
>> HE DIDN'T COME OUT AS RAMI,
THEN GO INTO FREDDIE.
HE STOMPED OUT AND IT WAS JUST
LIKE, "OH MY GOD, THIS IS REALLY
GONNA WORK."
I THINK WE CRACKED IT, I THINK.
WE ARE THE CHAMPIONS
>> THERE'S NO OSCAR FOR BEST
SUPPORTING TEETH - BUT ANOTHER
BIG WIN FOR RAMI MALEK TONIGHT
--
♪ TO OF THE WORLD ♪
>> -- WILL UNDOUBTEDLY LEAVE HIM
ALL SMILES.
NEXT, FAREWELL.
>> TONIGHT JIMMY SAYS SARDINE
SURPRISE.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
>> WELL, JIMMY GETS A BIG FAT
COMMISSION.
to severe plaque psoriasis.
With TREMFYA®, you can get
clearer.
And stay clearer.
In fact, most patients who saw
90% clearer skin at 28 weeks
stayed clearer through 48 weeks.
TREMFYA® works better than
Humira® at providing clearer
skin
and more patients were symptom
free with TREMFYA®.
TREMFYA® may lower
your ability
to fight infections and may
increase
your risk of infections.
Before treatment,
your doctor should check you for
infections and tuberculosis.
Tell your doctor if you have an
infection
or have symptoms such as:
fever, sweats, chills, muscle
aches or cough.
Before starting TREMFYA®
tell your doctor if you plan to
or have recently received a
vaccine.
Ask your doctor about TREMFYA®.
TREMFYA®. Because you deserve to
stay clearer.
Janssen wants to help you
explore cost support options.
The in-laws have moved in
with us.
And our adult children are here.
So we save by using Tide.
Which means we use less.
Three generations of clothes
cleaned in one wash.
Anybody seen my pants?
#1 stain and odor fighter, #1
trusted.
It's got to be Tide.
>> Pauley: IT HAPPENED THIS PAST
WEEK, THE LOSS OF THREE SHOWMEN
IN VERY DIFFERENT WORLDS.
KARL LAGERFELD WAS A GIANT IN
FASHION -- CHOSEN IN 1983 TO
UPDATE THE LEGENDARY HOUSE OF
COCO CHANEL.
>> CHANEL WAS SOMETHING DOWDY
FOR MIDDLE-AGED WOMEN WHO HAD NO
SENSE FOR FASHION OR NOT THE
BODIES TO WEAR IT.
LAGERFELD TURNED CHANEL'S
SAGGING FORTUNES AROUND.
AND HE REMAINED ITS CREATIVE
DIRECTOR UNTIL HIS DEATH IN
PARIS THIS PAST TUESDAY.
HE ONCE
OBSERVED, "SWEATPANTS ARE A SIGN
OF DEFEAT".
>> KARL LAGERFELD WAS, WELL,
WIDELY BELIEVED TO BE 85.
>> Pauley: PETER TORK WAS A
STRUGGLING CLUB MUSICIAN WHEN HE
WON A SPOT ON "THE MONKEES" TV
SHOW ♪
♪ HAY, WE ARE THE MONKEYS
>> Pauley: WHICH PREMIERED IN
1966.
TORK JOINED CO-STARS MICKY
DOLENZ, MIKE NESMITH, AND THE
LATE DAVY JONES AS MEMBERS OF A
QUIRKY ROCK BAND.
BUT THERE WAS NOTHING FUNNY
ABOUT TORK'S REACTION TO THE
PRODUCERS' RELIANCE ON STUDIO
MUSICIANS FOR THE MONKEES' EARLY
RECORDS:
>> I WAS MORTIFIED.
I HAD STUDIED MUSIC, AND I
BROUGHT IT TO THEM AND THEY
SAID, "NO, NO. YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND.  THIS IS THE RECORD.
IT'S ALL DONE. WE DON'T NEED
YOU."
>> STILL, BY THEIR THIRD ALBUM,
"THE MONKEES" WERE PERFORMING
ALMOST ALL THEIR OWN MUSIC.
AND EVEN AFTER THE SHOW WENT OFF
THE AIR IN 1968, THE MONKEES
REUNITED FOR TOURS, MOST
RECENTLY IN 2016.
PETER TORK WAS 77.
>> Pauley: AND WE LEARNED THIS
OSCAR WEEKEND OF THE DEATH OF
STANLEY DONEN, THE DIRECTOR OF
"SINGIN' IN THE RAIN" AMONG
OTHER CLASSIC HOLLYWOOD
MUSICALS.
AN ACCOMPLISHED SONG-AND-DANCE
MAN IN HIS OWN RIGHT.
NOTE I AM IN HEAVEN, I AM IN
HEAVEN
>> Pauley: DONEN ACCEPTED AN
HONORARY OSCAR IN 1998 AS ONLY
HE COULD:
WHEN WE ARE DANCING CHEEK TO
CHEEK.
>> STANLEY DONEN WAS 94.
>> Pauley: STILL TO COME - THE
HARVEY GIRLS - A REAL STATION
BREAK.
>> ALL ABOARD!
Here's your Buick sir.
Actually, that's my Buick.
Your Buick doesn't have a
roof rack!
This is my Buick.
How are we gonna fit in your
mom's Buick?
Easy.
I like that new Buick.
Me too.
I was actually talking about
that Buick.
I knew that.
Did you?
Buick's fresh new lineup is full
of surprises.
Get great deals on our
expectation-shattering lineup.
Pay no interest for 72 months
on most Buick models.
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
♪ ON THE TOPEKA, AND THE TOPEKA
AND THE SANTA FE!
>> Pauley: THAT'S JUDY GARLAND,
0 TAKING A STATION BREAK, A
RAILROAD STATION BREAK ONE WITH
ITS OWN
OSCAR-WINNING SONG.
ALL BASED ON A TRUE STORY.
HERE'S MICHELLE MILLER.
>> WOO!
>> LAST FALL, A CHEER WENT UP AS
A GRAND HOTEL FROM A BYGONE ERA.
>> HELLO!
>> GOT A LITTLE CLOSER TO
OPENING ITS DOORS.
>> WHEN THE HOTEL WAS BUILT IN
1898, THERE WERE A DOZEN
TRANSCONTINENTAL PASSENGER
TRAINS STOPPING HERE EVERY DAY.
ALL THE TRAIN PASSENGERS WOULD
COME ROLLING OFF THE TRAINS.
>> THIS IS THE ENTRYWAY.
THEY WOULD COME IN THIS WAY, AND
THEY WOULD WALK THROUGH THIS
DOOR TO GET INTO THE LUNCHROOM.
>> FOR ALLAN AFFELDT, RESTORING
LA CASTANEDA, IN LAS VEGAS, NEW
MEXICO, IS A LABOR OF LOVE.
>> SO THIS WAS THE MAIN DINING
ROOM, AND OF COURSE IT WAS ONE
OF THE BIGGEST, FANCIEST
RESTAURANTS IN ALL OF NORTHERN
NEW MEXICO.
>> ONE OF THE LAST VESTIGES OF A
VAST NETWORK OF HOTELS AND
RESTAURANTS THAT ONCE STRETCHED
ACROSS THE SOUTHWEST, ALL BUILT
BY THE FRED HARVEY COMPANY.
>> THERE WERE ALL THESE OTHER
HOTEL COMPANIES, RIGHT, THAT
STANDARDIZED THINGS, LIKE HOWARD
JOHNSON'S, AND EVENTUALLY
HILTONS AND HYATTS AND MARRIOTTS
AND ALL THAT.
>> BUT IT ALL --
>> FRED HARVEY WAS THE FIRST
ONE.
>> OH, WOW.
>> SO THIS ROOM IS CALLED --
>> THIS IS THE SANTA FE ROOM.
>> DIANA CLANIN IS A DOCENT AT
LA FONDA, IN SANTA FE, ONE OF A
HANDFUL OF FRED HARVEY HOTELS
STILL IN OPERATION.
>> EVERYWHERE YOU SEE A CITY
ALMOST THERE WAS A HARVEY HOUSE.
SOME OF THEM HAVE BEEN AS SIMPLE
AS A LUNCHROOM, SOME OF THEM MAY
HAVE BEEN LIKE THE LA FONDA, A
LUNCH ROOM, A RESTAURANT, AND A
HOTEL.
>> AN EMPIRE BUILT BY AN
IMMIGRANT FROM ENGLAND WHO SAW A
NEED FOR GOOD FOOD ALONG THE
NATION'S EXPANDING RAILROAD
LINES.
>> I THINK HE UNDERSTOOD AMERICA
BETTER THAN A LOT OF AMERICANS
DID AT THAT TIME.
>> STEPHEN FRIED'S BOOK TELLS
FRED HARVEY'S STORY.
>> HE WAS A TRAVELLING SALESMAN
FOR THE RAILROADS.
AND HE KNEW HOW TERRIBLE THE
FOOD WAS, ESPECIALLY WEST OF
CHICAGO.
AND SO I JUST THINK HE JUST FELT
THAT IF HE COULD DO IT WELL,
THAT WOULD CHANGE THINGS.
>> HE TOOK HIS IDEA TO THE
ATCHISON, TOPEKA AND SANTE FE
RAILROAD, THEN THE SMALLEST OF
THE COMPETING LINES.
>> FRED HARVEY SAID, WELL, IF I
HAVE BETTER FOOD, MAYBE MY
RAILROAD WILL WIN.
>> AND IN FACT THAT'S WHAT
HAPPENED.
>> FRED HARVEY RESTAURANTS
SPRANG UP AS FAST AS THE
RAILROAD COULD BUILD THEM, WITH
GOOD, FRESH FOOD PREPARED BY
WORLD-CLASS CHEFS, GOOD CHINA,
AND WHITE LINEN TABLECLOTHS.
>> YOU'D HAVE LONDON QUALITY
FOOD, NEW YORK-QUALITY FOOD IN
THE MIDDLE OF NEW MEXICO.
>> HOW ON EARTH WERE THEY ABLE
TO KEEP THAT LEVEL, THAT HIGH A
LEVEL OF QUALITY CONTROL?
>> THE TRAINS BROUGHT IN FRESH
FOOD FROM ALL THESE DIFFERENT
PLACES.
THEY REFRIGERATED IT.
YOU COULD BRING OYSTERS ALL THE
WAY FROM NEW YORK TO ARIZONA.
>> TOP QUALITY FOOD THAT WAS
SERVED TO EVERYONE.
AT A TIME WHEN THAT WASN'T SO
POPULAR.
>> WHEN YOU'RE ON THE TRAIN,
EVERYBODY'S ON THE TRAIN.
ALL COLORS, ALL CLASSES.
UM, EVERYBODY STAYS IN THE
HOTELS WHEN THEY'RE TRAVELING.
EVERYBODY EATS IN THE TRACKSIDE
RESTAURANTS.
>> ADD TO THAT PERFECT SERVICE
PROVIDED BY YOUNG, SMILING WOMEN
IN CRISP WHITE APRONS, WHO CAME
WEST BY THE THOUSANDS TO WORK
FOR THE FRED HARVEY COMPANY.
>> THEY HAD THE BRAVERY TO LEAVE
THEIR SMALL TOWNS, AND TO TRAVEL
ON THE TRAIN.
>> THESE WERE UNIQUE WOMEN.
>> PERFECTION IN THE DINING
ROOM, PERFECTION IN THE DORM.
WE EVEN WANT PERFECTION IN THE
HARVEY UNIFORM.
>> THEY BECAME KNOWN AS THE
HARVEY GIRLS, MEMORIALIZED BY
JUDY GARLAND IN 1946.
COME THUNDER, COME LIGHTNING,
COME DRIZZLE, COME SLEET, COME
CYCLONES, COME EARTHQUAKES, THE
PEOPLE GOTTA EAT!
>> WITH A SONG BY JOHNNY MERCER
THAT WON THE OSCAR.
ON THE ATCHISON TOPEKA AND THE
SANTA FE!
>> ALL ABOARD!
>> A FILM THAT DELIGHTS FRED
HARVEY'S GREAT GRANDCHILDREN TO
THIS DAY.
>> DO YOU HEAR THAT--WHISTLE
DOWN THE LINE?
>> KEEP GOING!
>> I RECKON THAT IT'S ENGINE
NUMBER 49.
IT'S THE ONLY ONE THAT SOUNDS
THAT WAY ON THE --
-- ATCHISON, TOPEKA AND THE
SANTA FE.
>> THEY WERE ONE OF AMERICA'S
FIRST FEMALE LABOR FORCES.
AND THAT IS REALLY REMARKABLE.
>> THE HARVEY GIRLS, AS THEY
WERE CALLED, LEFT AN INDELIBLE
MARK ON THE AMERICAN WEST.
DOCUMENTARIAN KATRINA PARKS SAYS
THE FRED HAVEY COMPANY WAS AHEAD
OF ITS TIME IN GIVING WOMEN THE
OPPORTUNITY TO WORK, AND ALSO TO
ESCAPE THE STRICT CONFINES OF
HOME.
>> I SEE THEM AS EARLY FEMINISTS
IN SOME WAYS, UM, EVEN THOUGH
THEY WOULDN'T HAVE, PERHAPS,
IDENTIFIED THAT WAY.
>> BUT WOULD YOU SAY THEY
CIVILIZED THE WEST?
>> I WOULDN'T USE THAT TERM.
>> BUT I MEAN IT, DID THEY TAMP
DOWN THE TESTOSTERONE?
>> SURE.
I THINK YOU CAN -- YOU CAN SAY
THAT, FOR SURE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> THE FRED HARVEY COMPANY ALSO
HIRED A WOMAN TO BE THEIR MAIN
ARCHITECT, THE BRILLIANT, AND
INTIMIDATING MARY COLTER, WHO
DESIGNED MANY OF FRED HARVEY'S
GRAND HOTELS AND INVENTED WHAT
WE NOW THINK OF AS SANTA FE
STYLE.
>> I NEVER SAW MY FATHER AFRAID
OF MUCH.
>> FRED HARVEY'S GREAT-GRANDSON,
CHARLES DAGGETT HARVEY, JR,
REMEMBERS HER WELL.
>> EVEN WHEN HE WOULD DESCRIBE
THE KAMIKAZE ATTACKS OFF OF
OKINAWA, HE DIDN'T SPEAK OF THAT
WITH FEAR.
BUT WHEN WE SPOKE OF MARY
COLTER, IT WAS AWE.
>> FOR MORE THAN FIFTY YEARS,
THE HARVEY COMPANY KEPT
EXPANDING, DEVELOPING THE GRAND
CANYON, AND OPENING AMERICA'S
EYES TO TOURISM, AND THE WONDERS
OF THE WEST.
>> PEOPLE GET FASCINATED WITH
AMERICA, WANTING TO EXPERIENCE
THE EXOTIC PARTS OF THE WEST
THAT HAD TO DO WITH SEEING
NATIVE AMERICANS, TO EXPERIENCE
DIFFERENT KINDS OF FOOD, TO SEE
OBVIOUSLY, THE HUGE, BIG SKY OUT
HERE, WHICH IS SO AMAZING.
>> HAVE YOU MET MR. HARVEY?
>> I -- YOU'RE MR. HARVEY, HOW
ARE YOU?
>> WELCOME.
>> EVERY YEAR --
>> BEST SMILE.
>> -- FRED HARVEY FANS -- THEY
CALL THEMSELVES FRED-HEADS --
>> WE STAYED HERE, LA FONDA.
>> -- GATHER TO HONOR THE HARVEY
FAMILY LEGACY.
>> I JUST WANNA WELCOME
EVERYBODY HERE.
>> AT LA FONDA, THERE WAS A
DINNER, PREPARED BY SANTA FE'S
TOP CHEFS.
>> BEAUTIFUL!
>> INSPIRED BY FRED HARVEY'S
CLASSIC RECIPES.
>> AND WE WORKED RIGHT HERE AT
LA FONDA.
>> YOU WORKED HERE?
>> RIGHT HERE.
IN THE FIFTIES.
>> AMONG THE GUESTS, FORMER
HARVEY GIRLS, INCLUDING TWINS
BEVERLY AND BERNETTE NYSTROM.
>> WE'VE JUST BECOME SO MUCH A
FAMILY WITH THE HARVEYS, SINCE
WE ARE PART OF HISTORY NOW.
>> A FAMILY THAT APPEARS TO BE
GROWING EVERY YEAR, AS MORE AND
MORE PEOPLE REDISCOVER THE
UNIQUELY AMERICAN STORY OF FRED
HARVEY AND THE EMPIRE HE BUILT.
>> Pauley: COMING UP
>> LET'S GO.
>> Pauley:  MOXIE, THE DOG WITH,
WELL, MOXIE.
METASTATIC BREAST
CANCER IS RELENTLESS,
BUT I'M RELENTLESS TOO.
MBC DOESN'T TAKE A DAY
OFF, AND NEITHER WILL I.
AND I TREAT MY MBC WITH
EVERYDAY VERZENIO-
THE ONLY ONE OF ITS KIND
THAT CAN BE TAKEN EVERY DAY.
IN FACT, VERZENIO IS
A CDK4 & 6 INHIBITOR
FOR POSTMENOPAUSAL WOMEN
WITH HR+, HER2-
METASTATIC
BREAST CANCER,
APPROVED, WITH
HORMONAL THERAPY,
AS AN EVERYDAY
TREATMENT
FOR A RELENTLESS
DISEASE.
VERZENIO + AN AI IS
PROVEN TO HELP WOMEN
HAVE SIGNIFICANTLY MORE TIME
WITHOUT DISEASE PROGRESSION,
AND MORE THAN HALF OF WOMEN SAW
THEIR TUMORS SHRINK VS AN AI.
DIARRHEA
IS COMMON,
MAY BE SEVERE,
AND MAY CAUSE
DEHYDRATION
OR INFECTION.
BEFORE TAKING VERZENIO,
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU HAVE
FEVER, CHILLS, OR OTHER
SIGNS OF INFECTION.
VERZENIO MAY CAUSE LOW
WHITE BLOOD CELL COUNTS,
WHICH MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS INFECTION
THAT CAN LEAD TO DEATH.
SERIOUS LIVER
PROBLEMS CAN OCCUR.
SYMPTOMS MAY INCLUDE TIREDNESS,
LOSS OF APPETITE, STOMACH PAIN,
AND BLEEDING OR BRUISING
MORE EASILY THAN NORMAL.
BLOOD CLOTS THAT CAN LEAD
TO DEATH HAVE ALSO OCCURRED.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU NOTICE PAIN OR SWELLING
IN YOUR ARMS OR LEGS,
SHORTNESS OF BREATH, CHEST PAIN
OR RAPID BREATHING
OR HEART RATE.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU ARE
PREGNANT, BREASTFEEDING,
OR PLAN TO BECOME PREGNANT.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
INCLUDE NAUSEA, INFECTIONS,
LOW RED AND WHITE BLOOD
CELLS AND PLATELETS,
DECREASED APPETITE, HEADACHE,
ABDOMINAL PAIN, TIREDNESS,
VOMITING, AND HAIR
THINNING OR LOSS.
I'M RELENTLESS.
AND MY DOCTOR AND I CHOOSE TO
TREAT
MY METASTATIC
BREAST CANCER
WITH VERZENIO.
BE RELENTLESS.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
EVERYDAY VERZENIO.
>> Pauley: FAR FROM HOLLYWOOD,
STEVE HARTMAN HAS THE PERFECT
NOMINEE FOR BEST SUPPORTING
PERFORMER.
>> IT TAKES REAL TENACITY TO
MAKE IT ON THE U.S. WOMEN'S SLED
HOCKEY TEAM.
BUT WHAT SETS 36-YEAR-OLD
CHRISTY GARDNER APART, AND WHAT
BROUGHT US HERE TO LEWISTON,
MAINE - ISN'T HER DOGGEDNESS -
IT'S HER DOG.
>> LET'S GO.
>> THIS IS MOXIE, CHRISTY'S
SERVICE DOG - AND HER HERO.
>> SHE'S ABSOLUTELY BEEN A LIFE
SAVER.
>> YOU MEAN THAT LITERALLY.
>> QUITE LITERALLY.
THAT DOG SAVED MY LIFE.
>> HERE YOU GO, KIDDO.
>> CHRISTY, AN ARMY VET, LOST
BOTH HER LEGS AFTER AN ATTACK
OVERSEAS.
>> GOOD GIRL.
>> SHE GOT MOXIE TO HELP WITH
DAILY TASKS.
BUT MORE IMPORTANTLY, DURING HER
DARKEST DAYS, CHRISTY SAYS HER
GOLDEN RETRIEVER WAS THE ONLY
THING THAT STOPPED HER FROM
ENDING HER OWN LIFE.
>> THE WAY SHE WOULD JUST LOOK
AT YOU.
HER EYES WOULD GO RIGHT THROUGH
TO YOUR SOUL.
AND I FELT LIKE I WAS
DISAPPOINTING HER.
AND SO HAVING HER BY MY SIDE WAS
THE ONLY REASON I DIDN'T KILL
MYSELF.
>> CHRISTY IS NOW MUCH BETTER,
BUT SHE HAS FELT INDEBTED TO HER
DOG EVER SINCE.
>> I FEEL LIKE SHE DESERVES SO
MUCH MORE.
>> UNFORTUNATELY, THERE IS NO
GOOD WAY TO REPAY A DEBT TO A
DOG --
>> YOU MY BEST BUDDY?
>> -- ESPECIALLY NOT THE
MAGNITUDE OF DEBT CHRISTY FEELS
SHE OWES MOXIE.
WHICH IS WHY, INSTEAD OF PAYING
IT BACK, SHE HAS COME UP WITH
THE SWEETEST PLAN - TO PAY IT
FORWARD.
MEET TINY TIM.
HE'S NOT JUST ANY PUPPY.
HE'S A PUPPY LIKE HER.
COME BACK TO CLASS
>> CHRISTY HAS TAKEN TIM AND HIS
BUM WING UNDER HER WING AND IS
NOW TRAINING THE PUP TO BE A
THERAPY DOG.
WE ARE WORKING ON MANNERS
>> IDEALLY, SHE'D LIKE HIM TO
WORK FULL-TIME HERE AT LEEDS
ELEMENTARY -- HELPING KIDS WHO
FEEL BROKEN.
>> THERE IS JUST SO MUCH ABOUT
HIM THAT IS SO PERFECT FOR THIS
LITTLE MISSION OF HIS.
I THINK THE KIDS ARE GOING TO
SAY, WELL, HE HAD ALL THESE
PROBLEMS AND HE DIDN'T GIVE UP -
AND LOOK HOW HAPPY HE IS.
>> BUT BEFORE TIM CAN BE A
CERTIFIED THERAPY DOG, HE NEEDS
A SURGERY TO AMPUTATE HIS BAD
LEG.
CHRISTY HAD BEEN WORKING
MULTIPLE JOBS TO PAY FOR THAT -
UNTIL THIS ASSEMBLY.
>> A CHECK FOR $10,000 TO PAY
FOR ALL OF TINY TIM'S MEDICAL
EXPENSES.
[CHEERS]
>> VETRISCIENCE, A PET FOOD
SUPPLEMENT COMPANY, MADE THE
DONATION - DELIGHTING BOTH
TRAINER AND TRAINEE.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
>> LOOKS LIKE THAT DEBT HAS BEEN
REPAID - IN FULL.
MOXIE SAVES YOU.
YOU SAVE TINY TIM.
AND NOW TINY TIM IS GOING TO
SAVE THE TOWN.
[LAUGHTER]
>> IT'S PRETTY COOL.
>> VERY COOL - BUT ALSO,
EXHAUSTING.
>> YOU PUT PASTA?
WE'LL HAVE A GLASS CONTAINER
WITH PASTA.
>> Pauley: NEXT - DECORATED TO
SELL.
>> Pauley: BEHOLD OUR SUNDAY
MORNING SET:
BEFORE.
AND AFTER.
REIMAGINED BY A FILM
ACTRESS TURNED DETECT AREA
WHO HAS A STORY WORTHY OF A
MOVIE, AS ALINA CHO SHOWS US:
>> WE WANNA KEEP THIS OPEN, TO
THE VIEW.
>> HIGH UP IN THE HOLLYWOOD
HILLS, THIS MODERN 3-BEDROOM
HOME IS ABOUT TO GO ON THE
MARKET.
>> WE WANT PEOPLE TO WALK INTO
THIS SPACE AND FEEL AT HOME.
WHAT WE WANT IS FOR THEM TO WALK
IN THE FRONT DOOR, FALL IN LOVE,
AND JUST KNOW THAT IT'S IT.
IT'S LIKE WHEN YOU FIND THE
RIGHT MATE OR THE RIGHT PET.
>> MERIDITH BAER IS THE ULTIMATE
MATCHMAKER.
SHE HAS A PROVEN TRACK RECORD,
OF TAKING A HOME LIKE THIS ONE,
TOTALLY EMPTY, AND DRESSING IT
UP.
>> THE GOAL IS TO GET AS MANY
PROSPECTIVE BUYERS TO FALL IN
LOVE WITH IT AT FIRST SIGHT AND
MAKE AN OFFER.
YOU REALLY HAVE 12 SECONDS TO
CAPTURE THEM.
>> KONSTANTINE SHOULD KNOW.
HE'S ONE OF LA'S TOP REALTORS
AND THIS HOME IS ONE OF HIS
LISTINGS.
>> AND THAT'S WHERE ALL OF THIS
EFFORT IS 12 SECONDS LONG.
AND THEY'LL WALK IN, AND THEY'LL
GO TO THE STAIRS, AND THEY'LL
SAY: I'M DONE.
>> SERIOUSLY? IT'S HAPPENED?
>> IT HAPPENS EVERY DAY WITH ME.
>> BECAUSE --
>> WOW.
>> -- OF HER.
>> BECAUSE OF HER.
>> MM-HMM.
>> FIRST CHALLENGE: YOU WALK IN
AND THERE'S A WALL.
>> SO A CONSOLE?
>> A CONSOLE, AND PROBABLY
EITHER AN ART OR A MIRROR.
>> LORENA SEGURA IS ONE OF
MERIDITH BAER'S THREE DOZEN
DESIGNERS.
>> I WANNA DO RUGS IN HERE.
>> LAST YEAR, THE COMPANY STAGED
MORE THAN 2,000 HOMES
NATIONWIDE.
ACCORDING TO THE INDUSTRY,
STAGED HOMES SELL 76 PERCENT
FASTER, AND OFTEN, FOR TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS ABOVE THE
ASKING PRICE.
SOMETIMES, BAER DESIGNS FOR
CELEBRITY CLIENTELE, LIKE CHER.
AND TAYLOR SWIFT.
>> THE GRAND REVEAL.
>> OH, WOW, WOW.
I MEAN, THIS IS AMAZING RIGHT
HERE.
>> IN JUST 24 HOURS, SEGURA
TURNED AN EMPTY WALL INTO AN
INVITING ENTRANCE.
SO A BOWL FOR THE KEYS.
ALWAYS A BEAUTIFUL PIECE OF
SOMETHING LIVE.
YOU KNOW, WE LOVE ORCHIDS, MOSS.
AND THEN THE COFFEE TABLE, I
HAVE A 5-5-5.
THE LIVING ROOM WENT FROM DRAB
TO DRAMATIC.
>> AND THEN THE BARSTOOLS GO
HERE.
>> AND HERE IN THE KITCHEN --
ONE OF BAER'S TRIED AND TRUE
TRICKS.
>> YOU PUT PASTA HERE?
>> YEAH, LIKE WE'LL HAVE LIKE --
WE'LL HAVE A CLEAR GLASS
CONTAINER WITH PASTA.
>> CAREFULLY POSITIONED PROPS.
I MEAN, THE LEVEL OF DETAIL.
WHAT IS THIS?
>> THAT'S PESTO.
>> YOU'LL EVEN LEAVE AN OPEN
COOKBOOK OUT?
>> WE WANT SOMEONE TO BE READY
JUST TO SAY: YES, THIS IS ME.
I SEE MYSELF THERE DOING THIS.
>> IN THE DINING ROOM.
>> A LARGE TABLE'S GONNA MAKE
THE HOUSE FEEL LARGER.
I KNOW THAT SOUNDS
COUNTERINTUITIVE.
[MUSIC]
>> IT DID.
THE LARGE MIRROR HELPED, TOO.
HERE I SAW THAT YOU BROUGHT IN
ALL OF THIS WONDERFUL ART.
>> BAER ALSO SEDUCES BUYERS WITH
A LITTLE HUMOR.
IT COULD BE ANYTHING.
I REMEMBER ONE TIME I DID A
MASTER BEDROOM, AND I THREW A
NEGLIGEE ON THE BED, AND SHOES
ACROSS THE ROOM, AND A TIFFANY
BOX THAT HAD JUST BEEN OPENED.
>> CAN YOU COME TO MY HOUSE AND
MAKE MY BED LIKE THIS?
>> IT LOOKS AMAZING!
IT LOOKS AMAZING.
>> THE SELLER, JACOB WEBER, HAS
HIRED MERIDITH BAER TWICE
BEFORE.
>> THEY MADE IT LOOK LIKE, THIS
IS A MORNING SHOW.  I CAN'T
REFER TO SEX APPEAL.
OR CAN I?
>> YOU CAN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WELL, THEY MADE IT LOOK LIKE
PEOPLE HAVE A LOT MORE SEX IN
THAT HOUSE THAN HAD IT IN
BEFORE.
>> BAER SAYS SELLERS SPEND AS
LITTLE AS $5,000 FOR A STAGING.
AND AS MUCH AS $150,000.
WEBER'S COST? $14,500.
>> FOR THE $14,000, YOU'RE
PROBABLY GONNA MAKE BACK
$120,000, YOU KNOW.
SO IF YOU LIKE MONEY, THEN YOU
WOULD SPEND THE 14 GRAND.
>> THAT BUDGET WILL ALSO GET YOU
A COZY MAN CAVE.
>> THIS IS GONNA MEAN A LOT TO A
YOUNG, HOLLYWOOD COUPLE, TO HAVE
THEIR OWN SCREENING ROOM.
>> AND WEBER'S HOUSE DID SELL,
IN A LITTLE MORE THAN A MONTH,
FOR $100,000 ABOVE THE ASKING
PRICE.
>> YOU'VE NEVER HAD ANY FORMAL
DESIGN TRAINING?
>> I'VE NEVER TAKEN A CLASS, NOT
ONE.
>> AND YET, YOU HAVE "IT."
>> I ALWAYS KNOW THAT IF I COULD
JUST MOVE THAT A LITTLE TO THE
RIGHT, IT LOOKS BETTER, AND I
DON'T KNOW HOW I KNOW THAT.
>> INSTINCTIVE?
>> YES.
>> IN COLLEGE, BAER STARTED
MODELING AND APPEARING IN
COMMERCIALS.
THAT LED TO SMALL PARTS ON TV
AND IN MOVIES, WHICH LED TO
SCREENWRITING.
ONE OF HER FILMS STARRED A
THEN-UNKNOWN GEORGE CLOONEY.
>> CHARLES WANTS THE OLD ME, OR
A DIVORCE.
>> GREAT.
I GOT A TERRIFIC LAWYER.
>> FAST FORWARD TO 1998: SHE WAS
RENTING A HOME IN L.A. AND FIXED
IT UP SO BEAUTIFLLY, THE OWNER
SOLD IT OUT FROM UNDER HER.
>> I HAD 250 PLANTS AND NOWHERE
TO GO.
>> AND A HOUSEFUL OF FURNITURE.
>> YES.
AND SO I HAD A FRIEND WHO WAS
TRYING TO SELL A HOUSE THAT'D
BEEN ON THE MARKET FOR ABOUT A
YEAR.
AND IT WAS EMPTY.
AND I SAID, "OK, HOW ABOUT I
BRING ALL OF THESE PLANTS OVER
THERE?
>> SO SHE FIXED UP THAT HOME,
TOO, AND IT SOLD WITHIN A WEEK.
FOR $500,000 ABOVE THE ASKING
PRICE.
SUDDENLY, SHE HAD THE MAKINGS OF
A BUSINESS, BUT NO PLACE OF HER
OWN.
>> I WAS NOW HOMELESS.
SO I'D SAY, OKAY.
AND PART OF THE DEAL IS THAT
I'LL LIVE HERE AND I'LL GIVE YOU
A DISCOUNT.
BECAUSE I JUST LOVE MAKING
THINGS BEAUTIFUL, ANY HOUSE THAT
I LIVED IN WOULD SELL USUALLY
WITHIN WEEKS.
>> SO YOU WERE MOVING A LOT.
>> IT DID GET TO ME.
YOU NEVER QUITE FEEL SECURE.
YOU REALLY DON'T EVER KNOW HOW
YOUR DAY'S GONNA END AND START.
YOU HAVE NO CONTROL OVER YOUR
LIFE.
>> TIMES HAVE CHANGED.
TODAY, MERIDITH BAER IS THE
LARGEST HOME STAGER IN THE
COUNTRY, WITH A STAFF OF 250.
>> OFFICES IN FIVE CITIES?
>> RIGHT.
LA, SAN FRANCISCO, MIAMI,
HAMPTONS AND NEW YORK.
>> BAER'S OFFICE NEAR LOS
ANGELES SITS ABOVE A 200,000
SQUARE FOOT WAREHOUSE.
>> HOW QUICKLY CAN YOU MAKE A
COUCH?
>> IN A DAY.
WE KEEP THEM BY COLORS, SIZE.
>> MILES OF LAMPS, CHAIRS, RUGS,
FAKE FRUIT, FAKE FLOWERS, GOLDEN
BUDDHAS, JARS OF Q-TIPS AND
COTTON BALLS.
A FULL-TIME ARTIST --
THERE'S LAUNDRY, TOO.
-- BECAUSE SOMEONE'S GOT TO IRON
ALL THE SHEETS.
>> SO, WHAT IF A PROSPECTIVE
BUYER NOT ONLY WANTS THE HOUSE,
BUT EVERYTHING INSIDE, TOO?
>> IT'S FOR SALE.
EVERYTHING IS FOR SALE.
I ALWAYS SAID, "I WOULD SELL
ANYTHING EXCEPT FOR MY CAT."
>> THERE IS ONE OCCUPATIONAL
HAZARD: AFTER SEEING THE
TRANSFORMATION, SOMETIMES, THE
SELLER DECIDES TO STAY PUT, LIKE
ACTRESS SCARLETT JOHANSSON.
>> WE STAGED HER HOUSE AND THEN
SHE WENT: OH, I KINDA LIKE THIS
HOUSE NOW, AND TOOK IT OFF THE
MARKET.
DEAREST BRITAIN.
WE LOVE YOU.
MAYBE IT'S YOUR BIG HEARTS.
YOUR SENSE OF STYLE.
WELCOME TO BA100.
(BA100,
YOU'RE CLEAR FOR TAKE-OFF).
HOW YOU FOLLOW YOUR OWN PATH.
YOU'VE LED REVOLUTIONS...
OF ALL KINDS.
YET YOU WON'T SHOUT ABOUT IT.
IT'S JUST NOT IN YOUR NATURE.
INSTEAD, YOU'LL
QUIETLY MAKE HISTORY.
CAKE.
BEDS.
POETRY.
TROUBLE.
LOVE! HOPE!
AND RATHER A LOT OF TEA.
THE BEST OF BRITAIN,
FROM THE MOMENT
YOU STEP ON BOARD.
>> Pauley: SOMETHING IS
MISSING AT TONIGHT'S OSCARS.
HERE IS JIM GAFFIGAN.
>>
>> THERE IS NO HOST FOR THE
OSCARS THIS YEAR.
OH ,MY GOSH.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
NO HOST?
THAT SOUNDS LIKE ABSOLUTE CHAOS.
THAT WOULD BE LIKE A HORSELESS
CARRIAGE.
OR AN ELEVATOR WITHOUT AN
OPERATOR.
WHAT'S NEXT?
A CAR WITHOUT A CHAUFFEUR?
THAT WOULD BE CERTAIN DEATH.
SOMEONE'S GONNA DIE TONIGHT, YOU
PEOPLE!
HECK, I'LL WATCH THAT.
TALK ABOUT A NATIONAL EMERGENCY!
NO HOST!
THAT MEANS THERE WILL BE NO ONE
TO START THE SHOW.
THE SHOW WILL HAVE NO BEGINNING
AND FOLLOWING THAT LOGIC NO END!
THIS YEAR, THE OSCARS MAY NEVER
END!
WITHOUT A HOST THERE WILL BE NO
ONE TO JOKINGLY SAY NEAR THE END
OF THE TELECAST, "WE'RE HALFWAY
THROUGH, FOLKS."
[LAUGHTER]
>> NO OPENING MONOLOGUE WHICH
PEOPLE WILL CRITICIZE ONLINE FOR
BEING WAY TOO IRREVERENT, OR WAY
TOO BLAND, OR "THE WORST EVER".
THE OSCARS ARE JUST GONNA BE
GOOD-LOOKING PEOPLE GIVING
GOOD-LOOKING PEOPLE AWARDS FOR
PRETENDING TO BE OTHER
GOOD-LOOKING PEOPLE.
THANKFULLY EVEN WITHOUT AN OSCAR
HOST THERE WILL STILL BE THE RED
CARPET BEFORE THE SHOW WHERE
PEOPLE IN THOUSAND-DOLLAR
DRESSES WILL TELL US TO LIVE
MORE RESPONSIBLE LIVES.
MOST IMPORTANTLY, WE CAN FIND
OUT WHO IS WEARING WHO AND LEARN
WHAT PEOPLE THINK ABOUT THE
OSCARS NOT HAVING A HOST.
THERE IS NO HOST FOR THE OSCARS
THIS YEAR.
MAYBE IT MEANS NOTHING, BUT I
THINK IT'S A TREND.
NO HOST FOR THE OSCARS, NO
COMEDIAN AT THE WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT'S DINNER, NO
CASHIER AT THOSE AUTOMATIC
CHECKOUT LANES AT THE GROCERY
STORE.
IT'S OBVIOUS THE ROBOTS ARE
TAKING OVER.
THESE ARE TROUBLED TIMES.
THERE SHOULD BE A MOVIE ABOUT
THAT.
I'D VOTE FOR THAT.
>> Pauley: STILL TO COME
>> WHAT WAS IT LIKE DATING FRANK
SINATRA?
>> WELL, IT WAS WONDERFUL.
>> Pauley: THE LIFE AND LOVES
OF ANGIE DICKERSON.
>>
ANGIE DICKENSON.
Grandma!
(Gasp)
We're finally doing this.
Ha! I am so doing this.
We're really doing this!
You could be doing this
when you sail with the
#1 cruise line in Alaska,
Princess Cruises.
7-days from five-ninety-nine*.
Visit princess.com or call
1-800-PRINCESS.
This is the all-new
Chevy Silverado.
It's beautiful.
Beefy and mean looking.
It's the strongest, most
advanced Silverado ever.
The cab is bigger than
the last generation.
It's the first truck I've
seen make you look small.
But that's not all...
Whoo!
Oh my...
Whoa!
The Silverado has more cargo
volume than any competitor.
Very impressive.
Now, during the Chevy
Presidents Day Sales Event,
get 0% financing for 72 months
on this All-New Silverado.
Drive yours away
this Presidents Day.
>> Pauley: ANGIE DICKENSON A
STAR IF THERE EVER WAS ONE, THIS
MORNING SHE IS TALKING TO MO
ROCCA FOR OUR SUNDAY PROFILE.
>> IF YOU WERE A CRITIC, DOING A
REVIEW OF YOUR LIFE SO FAR WHAT
WOULD YOU SAY?
>>
>> OH MY GOD, THAT'S ONE LUCKY
BITCH!
[POLICE WOMAN THEME]
>> WELL, IT'S NOT EXACTLY LUCK
THAT'S HAD ANGIE DICKINSON
TURNING HEADS.
DURING A FILM AND TV CAREER
THAT'S DOUBLED --
>> TIGER, IF WE HAD MET BEFORE,
YOU'D HAVE REMEMBERED IT. RIGHT,
FELLAS?
>> -- AS A HALF CENTURY-LONG
MASTER CLASS IN THE ART OF
SEDUCTION.
>> DID YOU ENJOY BEING A SEX
SYMBOL?
>> UH, YES, I ENJOYED IT VERY
MUCH.
I WOULDN'T WANNA BE KNOWN ONLY
AS A SEX SYMBOL.
>> RIGHT.
>> I WANTED TO BE KNOWN AS AN
ACTRESS, AS EQUALLY, OR, EVEN
MORE SO.
LIKE MARILYN MONROE.
SHE WAS KNOWN AS THE
GREATEST--AND RIGHTLY SO--SEX
SYMBOL OF ALL TIME.
BOY, TRY TO DO SHAKESPEARE AFTER
THAT.
>> ANGIE WAS ALWAYS MORE
DOWN-TO-EARTH, ROUGH-AND-TUMBLE
THAN MARILYN.
>> FORGET IT.
>> YOU FORGET IT!
>> WILLING TO GO MANO-A-MANO
WITH A TOUGH GUY LIKE LEE
MARVIN.
DO YOU CONSIDER YOURSELF MORE OF
A BROAD, A DAME, OR A GAL?
>> OH, ALL OF THE ABOVE!
>> SHE WAS BORN ANGIE BROWN IN
SEPTEMBER, 1931 -- YES, SHE'S
87--IN KULM, NORTH DAKOTA.
POPULATION: AROUND 740.
>> I GREW UP GOING TO MOVIES.
MY DADDY WAS THE PROJECTIONIST.
SO WE GOT IN FOR FREE.
AND I LOVED MOVIES.
IT BURNED DOWN AND WE CRIED FOR
A WEEK.
>> OH, YOU CRIED FOR A WEEK.
>> OH, IT WAS--I DECIDED TO GIVE
UP MOVIES FOR LENT SINCE THE
MOVIE THEATER BURNED DOWN.
THAT WAS YOUR PENANCE.
>> YOU'RE BRINGING BACK SO MANY
MEMORIES OF--THAT I DON'T THINK
ABOUT NORMALLY.
>> AFTER THE FAMILY MOVED TO
CALIFORNIA, DICKINSON FOUND WORK
AS A SECRETARY AND COMPETED IN
BEAUTY PAGEANTS -- WHICH LED TO
A SPOT ON THE COLGATE COMEDY
HOUR.
>> AND JIMMY DURANTE WAS SINGING
WITH FRANK SINATRA.
THAT WAS IT.
I SAID: THIS IS FOR ME.
>> SHE APPEARED IN A BUNCH OF TV
WESTERNS, THEN IN 1959 STARRED
IN "RIO BRAVO," OPPOSITE HER
CHILDHOOD HERO, JOHN WAYNE.
>> SAY WHAT?
>> THAT YOU LOVE ME!
>> I SAID I'D ARREST YOU!
>> IT MEANS THE SAME THING. YOU
KNOW THAT.
YOU JUST WON'T SAY IT!
>> MY PARENTS WERE DEMOCRATS.
AND I WAS A DEMOCRAT.
AND JOHN WAYNE WAS A REPUBLICAN.
>> DID YOU HAVE SOME TREPIDATION
BEFORE YOU MET HIM THEN?
>> I HAD TREPIDATION ABOUT
GETTING TOO CLOSE TO HIM AND
ENDING UP DISCUSSING POLITICS.
RIGHT.
AND I WAS AFRAID THAT I--WAS
AFRAID THAT I WOULD GET TO LIKE
HIM, AND THAT WOULD BE A
PROBLEM.
WELL, THEY DID A PLAY.
>> STUNT MEN TAUGHT DICKINSON TO
PLAY POKER DECADES AGO.
>> WELL, THE PLAY WAS "THE GIN
GAME."
>> CUT. SHUT UP AND DEAL!
OK.
>> AND SHE'S STILL PLAYING.
>> I PLAYED FOR 35 YEARS WITH
THE GERSHWINS.
>> IN 1960, SHE CO-STARRED WITH
THE RAT PACK IN "OCEAN'S 11."
SHE ENDED UP DATING FRANK
SINATRA.
>> WE GOT VERY CLOSE TO GETTING
MARRIED IN 1964.
>> BUT SINATRA'S LATE NIGHT
LIFESTYLE WASN'T FOR HER.
>> HE SAID: YOU KNOW, I'M NOT
GOING TO MARRY AN ACTRESS.
AND I SAID, "WELL, I DON'T BLAME
YOU.
I WOULDN'T WISH THAT ON
ANYBODY.".
AND I ACTUALLY DIDN'T WANT TO
MARRY HIM.
SO I DIDN'T WANT HIM TO ASK ME
TO MARRY HIM, 'CAUSE I DIDN'T
WANNA SAY NO TO FRANK SINATRA.
>> THERE HAVE LONG BEEN RUMORS
THAT DICKINSON AND PRESIDENT
JOHN F. KENNEDY HAD AN AFFAIR,
RUMORS SHE'S CONSISTENTLY
DENIED.
>> THERE WAS NO REASON OR NO
GROUNDS FOR THINKING THAT I WAS
SEEING HIM, AND I WASN'T.
>> ALL RIGHT.  THEN CAN I JUST
ASK: DID HE EVER PUT THE MOVES
ON YOU?
>> NO.
I SAID, I LIKE IT HERE!
>> BUT IN 1964, A FUTURE
PRESIDENT--RONALD REAGAN--DID
SLAP DICKINSON ACROSS THE FACE
IN THE MOVIE "THE KILLERS".
>> WHICH ALSO STARRED JOHN
CASSAVETTES.
>> YOU'RE EAST, WEST, SOUTH.ùAND
MY NORTH.
[MUSIC]
>> YOUR CHEMISTRY WITH HIM IN
THAT MOVIE --
>> YEAH, WE LIKED EACH OTHER, I
MUST SAY.
>> DO YOU MEAN THAT YOU LIKED
EACH OTHER JUST WORKIN' WITH
EACH OTHER, OR THAT THERE WAS
MORE?
>> NO, WE LIKED EACH OTHER
AS--AS MAN AND WOMAN AND AS
ACTORS, NOT ROMANCE.
>> IT'S SOMETHING IN BETWEEN,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S NOT FALLING INTO BED--
EX-- EXACTLY.
>> --WITH EACH OTHER. BUT IT'S--
BUT IT'S MORE THAN JUST, "I LIKE
WORKING WITH YOU."
NO, IT'S MUCH CLOSER THAN THAT.
YEAH.  REALLY, REALLY LIKE EACH
OTHER. LIKE, IF THINGS WERE
DIFFERENT, WE'D GO OUT.
THAT'S CHEMISTRY.
YEAH. IT HAPPENS ON MOVIE SETS.
YOU KNOW, ATTRACTIVE PEOPLE.
["WHAT THE WORLD NEEDS NOW.ù"]
IN 1965, DICKINSON MARRIED ONE
OF THE COUNTRY'S MOST SUCCESSFUL
SONGWRITERS.
>> WHAT MADE YOU FALL FOR BURT
BACHARACH?
>> WELL, THAT'S VERY HARD TO
SUMMARIZE.
HE WAS SO DIFFERENT.
>> THEY SEPARATED IN 1976.
WAS THERE A VERY HAPPY PERIOD?
>> NOT TOO MUCH.
NOT TOO MUCH.
HE SHOULD NEVER HAVE BEEN
MARRIED.
>> IN HIS AUTOBIOGRAPHY,
BACHARACH FESSED UP TO HIS
INFIDELITY.
>> HE NEVER LOVED ME, I CAN TELL
YOU THAT RIGHT NOW-THE WAY ONE
LOVES.
HE LOVED IN HIS OWN WAY, WHICH
IS NOT TOO GOOD.
UH, AND, SO HE HAD NO RESPECT
FOR ME.
>> DID YOU LOVE HIM?
>> YEAH, I LIKED HIM A LOT.
>> AND ALL THE STARS THAT NEVER
WERE ARE PARKIN' CARS AND A
PUMPIN' GAS.ù
>>> BOMP, BOMP, BOMP!
>> POLICE! DON'T MOVE!
>> IN 1974, ANGIE BECAME SGT.
PEPPER-
>> DROP THE GUN!
>> SGT. PEPPER ANDERSON. ON
POLICE WOMAN.
>> DAVID GERBER WAS THE
PRODUCER. AND HE SAID, "DON'T
YOU WANNA BE A HOUSEHOLD NAME?"
I REALIZED I WANTED TO BE A
HOUSEHOLD NAME.
>> IS IT TRUE THAT THERE WAS A
SURGE IN APPLICATIONS FROM WOMEN
TO JOIN THE POLICE FORCE?
>> YES, THERE WAS A SURGE. AND A
LOT OF FAN LETTERS WITH THAT.
"I BECAME A COP BECAUSE OF YOU."
>> DICKINSON BECAME ALMOST AS
WELL KNOWN FOR HER APPEARANCES
ON "THE TONIGHT SHOW.".
HER CHEMISTRY WITH JOHNNY CARSON
WAS UNDENIABLE.
>> I LOVE MOVIES, I LOVE DINNER
PARTIES, I LOVE YOU.
>> WELL, YOU MEAN THAT IN A --
>> ISN'T HE A SWEETHEART?
>> IN A PLATONIC RELATIONSHIP,
YOU MEAN?
>> OH, ALRIGHT.
>> NOT A DEEP --
>> DID YOU AND JOHNNY EVER DATE?
>> UH-HUH. WE DID DATE.
>> WHO BROKE IT OFF?
>> THINGS HAPPEN.
>> ANGIE DICKINSON HAS ALWAYS
BEEN FRANK IN HER OPINIONS ON
SEXUAL MATTERS - INCLUDING THE
TOPIC THAT HAS ROILED HOLLYWOOD
FOR THE PAST TWO YEARS.
>> HEY, CAN I ASK: WHAT DO YOU
THINK OF THE METOO MOVEMENT?
>> I HATE IT. IT'S ALL OUT OF
PROPORTION-LIKE MY HAND.
I SAY: AN OPEN ROBE IS NOT A
RAPE.
LISTEN, I'M SURE MEN MISBEHAVED.
BUT I WASN'T THERE.
SHOULD WE GO ONE MORE?
>> SURE. YEAH.
>> DICKINSON LIVES ALONE NOW IN
BEVERLY HILLS.
["NIKKI" PLAYS.]
>> HER DAUGHTER NIKKI, FROM HER
MARRIAGE TO BURT BACHARACH, DIED
IN 2007.
>> WHAT ARE YOUR BEST MEMORIES
OF NIKKI, YOUR DAUGHTER?
>> SHE WAS VERY SMART AND FUNNY
AND WONDERFUL.
YEAH.
SO ALL THE MEMORIES OF HER ARE
MY BEST MEMORIES.
>> BORN THREE MONTHS PREMATURE,
NIKKI SUFFERED CHRONIC HEALTH
PROBLEMS, INCLUDING SEVERE
EYESIGHT LOSS AND ASPERGER'S
SYNDROME.
>> IF SHE HIT ME, SHE WOULD HIT
ME OUT OF FRUSTRATION, OF NOT
BEING ABLE TO COPE WITH WHATEVER
IT WAS WAS HER PROBLEM.
SHE HAD NO COPING SKILLS.
SO SHE JUST TOOK HER LIFE. SHE
COULDN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
>> NIKKI WAS 40 YEARS OLD.
>> SHE WAS A WONDERFUL,
WONDERFUL GIFT.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT WHEN
YOU LOOK OUT HERE?
>> THAT I HOPE THAT I NEVER DIE.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH, IT'S BEAUTIFUL, ISN'T
IT?
AND SOME DAY, I WON'T HAVE THIS.
BUT I WON'T KNOW IT.
>> THIS WEEK ON "MOBITUARIES."
THE NEANDERTHALS.
OUR ANCIENT COUSINS DON'T GET
MUCH RESPECT.
CAVEMEN!
CARICATURED AS BRUTISH.
[YELLING]
[HOWLING]
>> NOT TOO SMART.
IT'S SO EASY TO USE GEICO.COM, A
CAVEMAN CAN DO IT.
>> WHAT?
>> OH, NO, I--
>> NOT COOL.
>> I DID NOT--
>> TURNS OUT, NEANDERTHALS WERE
A LOT LIKE US.
>> THEY MADE A LOT OF THE SAME
KIND OF TOOLS, THEY HAD FIRE.
>> OH, AND THEY'RE STILL WITH
US.
>> IF THEY HAD TOLD ME ONLY HOW
MUCH NEANDERTHAL I AM, I WOULD
HAVE PAID TWICE THE AMONT FOR
THE TEST.
>> JOIN ME AND SPECIAL GUEST
MICHAEL IAN BLACK.
"MOBITUARIES"-WHEREVER YOU GET
YOUR PODCASTS.
>> BROUGHT TO YOU BY AWS.
>> Pauley: NEXT DAVID
EDELSTEIN GETS LAST WORD.
>>
together to deliver truly
personalized cancer care.
Expert medicine works here.
Learn more at
cancercenter.com.
Let's go.
Bye, Mom.
Thanks for breakfsat, Mom.
With quality ingredients like
roasted hazelnuts and cocoa,
Nutella is sure to bring a
smile to breakfast time.
♪
.
If you have moderate to
severe psoriasis,
little things
can be a big deal.
That's why there's Otezla.
Otezla is not a cream.
It's a pill that treats plaque
psoriasis differently.
With Otezla, 75% clearer skin
is achievable.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Otezla.
It may cause severe diarrhea,
nausea, or vomiting.
Otezla is associated with an
increased risk of depression.
Tell your doctor if you have a
history of depression
or suicidal thoughts
or if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor your
weight and may stop treatment.
Upper respiratory tract
infection
and headache may occur.
Tell your doctor about
your medicines,
and if you're pregnant
or planning to be.
Ready to treat differently
with a pill?
Otezla. Show more of you.
Ready to treat differently
with a pill?
Mom, Dinosaurs only eat Meat.
Actually, the biggest Dinos
only ate plants,
and Country Crock
is made with plants.
Country Crock has always
been made
with the goodness of plants.
It has real simple ingredients
and that same Country
fresh taste you love.
mmMMmmMMmm!
Welcome to Crock Country.
98% of us don't get enough
omega-3s.
Which is why MegaRed Advanced
4in1
packs more omega-3 power into
one small softgel.
It supports your heart...
Brain... Eyes... And joints.
MegaRed.
>> Pauley:  NOW, WITHOUT FURTHER
ADO, OUR DAVID EDELSTEIN.
>> NO MATTER HOW BADLY SOME OF
US SCREWED UP IN THE LAST YEAR,
THE FOLKS RUNNING THE OSCARS
SCREWED UP WORSE.
THEY ANNOUNCED A CATEGORY FOR
"POPULAR FILMS," AND IT WAS
POPULAR, ALL RIGHT--TO DUMP ON.
THEN THE CHOSEN HOST, KEVIN
HART, HAD HOMOPHOBIC RANTS IN
HIS PAST AND DOUBLED DOWN WHEN
HE SHOULD HAVE PROSTRATED
HIMSELF.
TO SHORTEN THE BROADCAST THEY
ANNOUNCED THEY'D GIVE SOME
AWARDS DURING COMMERCIALS.
PIDDLING STUFF, LIKE,
CINEMATOGRAPHY--THE PICTURES
PART OF MOVING PICTURES.
THAT LASTED FEWER DAYS THAN
KEVIN HART.
BUT THE MEANING IS CLEAR.
THE ACADEMY IS HAVING A CRISIS
OF CONFIDENCE.
WE ARE IN A CULTURE IN WHICH
EVERYONE'S ANGRY ABOUT HOW HE,
SHE, OR THEY IS BEING
REPRESENTED--NOT WITHOUT CAUSE.
NO MATTER WHICH OF THE EIGHT
NOMINEES FOR BEST PICTURE WINS,
SOMEONE WILL BE OFFENDED.
THE FRONT-RUNNERS ARE "GREEN
BOOK" AND "ROMA." I LIKED "GREEN
BOOK."
>> DO YOU FORESEE ANY ISSUES IN
WORKIN' FOR A BLACK MAN?
YOU IN THE DEEP SOUTH? THERE'S
GONNA BE PROBLEMS.
>> IT'S AMIABLE, IT'S WELL-MADE.
BUT IT'S ABOUT A WHITE RACIST-
>> YOU PEOPLE LOVE THE FRIED
CHICKEN.
>> YOU HAVE A VERY NARROW
ASSESSMENT OF ME, TONY.
>> --WHOSE CONSCIOUSNESS IS
RAISED ON A ROAD TRIP SOUTH,
COMING AT A TIME WHEN A STORY OF
RACISM FROM A WHITE POINT OF
VIEW IS NO LONGER CONSIDERED THE
SIGN OF A RAISED CONSCIOUSNESS.
IF "GREEN BOOK" WINS, SPIKE LEE
WILL HAVE FLASHBACKS TO HIS 1989
CLASSIC-
FIGHT THE POWERS THAT BE!
--"DO THE RIGHT THING" BEING
OVERLOOKED IN FAVOR OF ANOTHER
WHITE-CONSCIOUSNESS RAISING
FILM, "DRIVING MISS DAISY."
>> HELLO, THIS IS RON STALLWORTH
CALLING.
>> THIS IS DAVID DUKE, GRAND
WIZARD OF THE KU KLUX KLAN.
>> LEE'S FIRST-EVER DIRECTING
NOMINATION IS FOR
"BLACKKKLANSMAN," ALSO NOMINATED
FOR BEST PICTURE-
>> WHAT CAN I DO YA FOR?
>> WELL, SINCE YOU ASKED, I HATE
BLACKS.
>> --AND WITH A BLACK POINT OF
VIEW--THOUGH ONE OF ITS HEROES
IS JEWISH, WHICH CAN'T HURT.
IT COULD SNEAK IN.
SINGIN' WE WILL, WE WILL ROCK
YOU.
"BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY," WHICH I
ALSO LIKED, HAS NO CHANCE,
PARTLY BECAUSE DIRECTOR BRYAN
SINGER IS ACCUSED OF ALL SORTS
OF ABUSES.
BUT RAMI MALEK IS A LOCK.
OUR LEAD SINGER JUST QUIT.
THEN YOU'LL NEED SOMEONE NEW.
WE ARE THE CHAMPIONS
ALSO A LOCK: HE WON'T THANK HIS
DIRECTOR.
UH, THE VICE PRESIDENCY IS
MOSTLY A, UH, SYMBOLIC JOB.
>> HOLLYWOOD LIBERALS LIKED
"VICE," MOSTLY FOR CHRISTIAN
BALE'S PORTRAIT OF DICK CHENEY
AS A FROGGY WAR CRIMINAL, BUT IT
HAS ZERO TRACTION.
>> HEY.
>> WHAT?
>> I JUST WANTED TO TAKE ANOTHER
LOOK AT YOU.
>> NOR, SURPRISINGLY, HAS
BRADLEY COOPER'S MEGA-HIT "A
STAR IS BORN."
>> THE ROUSING SMASH "BLACK
PANTHER" IS THE FIRST MARVEL
SUPERHERO BEST PICTURE
NOMINATION, BUT MOST HOLLYWOOD
TYPES THINK IT'S THERE BECAUSE
THE ACADEMY WAS AFRAID NOT TO
NOMINATE THE MOST SUCCESSFUL
FILM BY A BLACK DIRECTOR OF ALL
TIME.
"THE FAVOURITE" IS ALSO A BLAST.
>> LET'S SHOOT SOMETHING.
>> BUT IT'S EVERYBODY'S SECOND
FAVORITE.
SO, ALFONSO CUARON'S "ROMA,"
ACQUIRED BY NETFLIX, BARELY
RELEASED IN THEATERS.
IT BREAKS MY HEART THAT 99% OF
YOU WILL SEE THIS HAUNTING,
BEAUTIFUL BUT NOT NARRATIVELY
GRIPPING MOVIE ON THE SAME
SCREEN YOU'RE SEEING ME ON NOW.
IT SHOULD ENVELOP YOU.
IT WILL LIKELY WIN, BUT MANY
PEOPLE WILL THINK HOLLYWOOD IS
PICKING A SPANISH-LANGUAGE FILM
ABOUT A MAID TO SIGNAL ITS
VIRTUE YET AGAIN.
BET ON REGINA KING IN "IF BEALE
STREET COULD TALK" AND EITHER
MAHERSHALA ALI FOR GREEN BOOK OR
RICHARD E. GRANT FOR "CAN YOU
EVER FORGIVE ME?"--BOTH PLAYING
GAY CHARACTERS.
TOO CLOSE TO CALL.
BUT GLENN CLOSE IS A BEST
ACTRESS LOCK FOR THE FEMINIST
DRAMA "THE WIFE"-
>> DON'T PAINT ME AS A VICTIM.
I AM MUCH MORE INTERESTING THAN
THAT.
>> PARTLY BECAUSE OF ALL THOSE
NOMINATIONS SHE'S HAD, PARTLY
BECAUSE IT IS THE SUBTLEST,
SMARTEST, MOST POIGNANT
PERFORMANCE I'VE SEEN IN A MOVIE
THAT DUMB.
AS I SAID, EVERYONE EXPECTS TO
HATE THIS YEAR'S OSCARS, WHICH,
MAYBE--WHO KNOWS?--MEANS IT'LL
BE MORE BAD FUN THAN ANY OSCARS
IN YEARS.
Get $200 off
select XPS13 laptops
at Dell.com
♪
It's easy to move forward
when you're ready
for what comes next.
At Fidelity, we make sure
you have a clear plan
to cover the essentials
in retirement,
as well as all the things
you want to do.
And on the way, you'll get
timely investment help
to keep you on the right track,
without the unnecessary fees
you might expect
from so many financial firms.
Because when you have a partner
who gives you clarity
at every step,
there's nothing to stop you
from moving forward.
who gives you clarity
at every step,
♪ When you have nausea, ♪
♪ heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, ♪
♪ upset stomach, ♪
♪ diarrhea... ♪
Girl, Pepto ultra coating will
treat your stomach right.
♪Nausea, heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, upset stomach,♪
♪ diarrhea... ♪
Try Pepto with Ultra coating.
♪
>> Pauley: HERE'S A LOOK AT THE
WEEK AHEAD, ON OUR "SUNDAY
MORNING" CALENDAR.
ON MONDAY, VETERAN CBS NEWS
CORRESPONDENT AND "FACE THE
NATION" ANCHOR EMERITUS BOB
SCHIEFFER TURNS 82.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, BOB!
TUESDAY MARKS THE 100th
ANNIVERSARY OF THE GRAND CANYON
BECOMING A NATIONAL PARK.
WEDNESDAY IS INTERNATIONAL POLAR
BEAR DAY, DRAWING ATTENTION TO
THE CHALLENGES POLAR BEARS FACE
IN A WARMING WORLD.
ON THURSDAY, PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
NORTH KOREAN LEADER KIM JONG-UN
CONCLUDE A TWO-DAY SUMMIT IN
VIETNAM.
FRIDAY KICKS OFF WOMEN'S HISTORY
MONTH.
THIS YEAR'S THEME: VISIONARY
WOMEN, CHAMPIONS OF PEACE AND
NON-VIOLENCE.
AND SATURDAY IS "READ ACROSS
AMERICA" DAY, CELEBRATING
CHILDREN'S BOOKS THAT REFLECT
THE DIVERSITY OF TODAY'S
STUDENTS AND READERS.
AND NOW TO MARGARET BRENNAN IN
WASHINGTON, FOR A LOOK AT WHAT'S
AHEAD ON "FACE THE NATION."
GOOD MORNING, MARGARET.
>> GOOD MORNING, TO YOU, JANE.
WE WILL LOOK AT THE BIGGEST
LEGAL AND POLITICAL THREAT TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP, ACCORDING TO
HIS LONG TIME STRATEGIST STEVE
BANNON.
>> Pauley: THANK YOU,
MARGARET.
AND NEXT WEEK HERE ON "SUNDAY
MORNING:"
>> IT SMELLS GOOD.
>> Pauley: SAY CHEESE!
>>
move to another treatment,
ask if XELJANZ XR
is right for you.
XELJANZ XR is a
once-daily pill
for adults with moderate
to severe RA for whom
methotrexate did not work
well enough
It can reduce pain, swelling
and further joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ XR can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis. Serious,
sometimes fatal infections,
and cancers, including
lymphoma, have happened.
As have tears in the stomach
or intestines,
serious allergic reactions,
low blood cell counts,
higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels.
Don't start XELJANZ XR if
you have an infection.
Your doctor should
perform blood tests before
and while taking XELJANZ XR,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you've
been somewhere fungal
infections are common
and if you have had TB,
hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Don't let another morning
go by without talking to
your rheumatologist about
XELJANZ XR.
It's time for the Ultimate
Sleep Number Event
on the Sleep Number
360 smart bed.
It senses your movement
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
Save 50% on the
Sleep Number 360
Limited Edition smart bed.
Plus, 24-month financing
on all smart beds.
Ends Sunday.
Almost time for me to go.
Well, what if I...
drove me home?
[♪]
What if we lost track of time?
What if we took a leap of faith?
Whoo-hoo!
What if you...
missed my flight next week?
[♪]
The All-New RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
Unpredictable Crohn's
symptoms following you?
For adults with moderately
to severely active
Crohn's disease,
STELARA® works differently.
Studies showed
relief and remission,
with dosing every 8 weeks.
STELARA® may lower your
ability to fight infections
and may increase your risk
of infections and cancer.
Some serious infections
require hospitalization.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if
you have an infection
or flu-like symptoms or sores,
have had cancer, or
develop new skin growths,
or if anyone in your house
needs or recently
had a vaccine.
Alert your doctor of new
or worsening problems,
including headaches, seizures,
confusion and vision problems.
These may be signs of a rare,
potentially fatal
brain condition.
Some serious allergic reactions
and lung inflammation
can occur.
Talk to your doctor today,
and learn how
Janssen can help you
explore cost support options.
Remission can start
with STELARA®.
>> IF YOU CAN'T SEE US, HEAR US,
ON OUR "SUNDAY MORNING" PODCAST.
SPONSORED BY PRUDENTIAL.
BRING YOUR CHALLENGES.
>> Pauley: WE LEAVE YOU THIS
SUNDAY MORNING WELL TO THE NORTH
OF HOLLYWOOD, IN MONTEREY BAY,
WHERE PACIFIC SEA NETTLES ARE
THE STARS.
>> Pauley: I'M JANE PAULEY.
PLEASE JOIN US WHEN OUR TRUMPET
SOUNDS AGAIN, NEXT "SUNDAY
MORNING."
Captioning made possible
by Johnson & Johnson,
committed to improving health
for everyone, everywhere.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org