MARKET
>> DAN SUZUKI.
>> HEALTH CARE, PROFITS ARE
SLOWING AND A GOOD TIME TO OWN
IT'S CHEAP AND THE BEST
LONG-TERM PERFORMING SECTORS OUT
THERE.
>> KAREN FINERMAN.
>> WHAT HE SAID AND WITH MORE
SPECIFICITY.
ANTHEM CALLS
>> UNICORN GUY
>> I HAVE TO THANK -- THE CRACK
STAFF, KELLY CAME TO THE HOUSE
AND SHE BROUGHT DOUGHNUTS AND
BAGELS AND THE WHOLE THING
A LOT OF FUN
WYNN RESORTS
>> YES, ONE MORE THING
KATE AND WILLIAM
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
MY TWINS ARE NOW BIG TWINS
>> HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
>> THAT DOES IT FOR US AND SEE
YO>>> MY MISSION IS SIMPLE
TO MAKE YOU MONEY.
I'M HERE TO LEVEL THE PLAYING
FIELD FOR ALL INVESTORS.
THERE IS ALWAYS A BULL MARKET
SOMEWHERE.
AND I PROMISE TO HELP YOU FIND
IT
"MAD MONEY" STARTS NOW
>>> HEY, I'M CRAMER.
WELCOME INTO "MAD MONEY.
WELCOME TO CRAMERICA
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE FRIENDS
JUST MAKE YOU MONEY.
MY JOB IS TO EDUCATE AND TEACH
YOU AND PUT INTO CONTEXT SO CALL
ME AT 800-743-CNBC OR TWEET ME
AT JIM CRAMER.
IF YOU WANT TO GET AN HONEST
READ ON THE ECONOMY, FORGET THE
GOVERNMENT DATA FROM THE
COMMERCE DEPARTMENT OR THE
FEDERAL RESERVE.
INSTEAD YOU NEED TO LOOK AT THE
TRANSPORTS
ESPECIALLY THE RAILS
>> ALL ABOARD --
>> ON A BLAH DAY WHERE THE DOW
DIPPED 3 POINTS AND S&P AND
NASDAQ UP -- YOU HAVE AN
INCREDIBLE SNAPSHOT OF THE
ECONOMY FROM CSX AND STOCK THAT
CAUGHT FIRE TODAY.
YOU RECOGNIZE THE ECONOMY IS
SLOW IN THE FOURTH QUARTER, I
LOOKED AT THIS STUFF
THAT IS RIGHT.
JUST WHEN FED CHIEF SAID IT WAS
FIRING ON ALL CYLINDERS SO HE
NEEDED TO SLAM THE BRAKES BY
RAISING INTEREST RATES, I DID
THE HOMEWORK AND CHECK IN WITH
THE CHEMICALS AND PAPERS AND
HOLD BUILDERS AND THE TRANSPORTS
ESPECIALLY THE RAILS
SEE, THE RAILS WERE TELLING ME A
DIFFERENT STORY FROM THE ROSIE
ECONOMIC FORECAST.
I HAD TO PUT IT INTO A MOSAIC BY
HAND AND IT SHOWED THE ECONOMY
IS SLOWING BECAUSE THE FED HAS
GOTTEN TOO AGGRESSIVE AND NOT
ACCELERATING BECAUSE THE FED
HADN'T DONE ENOUGH
I'M GLAD POWELL CHANGED HIS MIND
BUT IT FEELS LIKE THE PEOPLE ON
THE FEDERAL RESERVE DIDN'T WANT
TO GET THEIR HANDS DIRTY ON THE
CALLS FROM THE COMPANIES
AND SOME BRANCHS IN ST. LOUIS,
HIGH QUALITY SEARCH BUT TODAY WE
HAVE THE BASE BOOK WITH GOOD
NUGGETS.
BUT IT IS NOT AS GOOD AS WHAT
YOU COULD ASSEMBLE FOR YOURSELF
BY KNOWING WHICH COMPANIES HAVE
THEIR FINGERS ON THE PULSE OF
THE ECONOMY AND THEY ARE BACKED
UP BY COLD, HARD CASH AND
RECEIPTS AND MANIFEST.
WHAT IS IT TELLING ME NOW, I
THINK WE HAVE A GOLDILOCKS
ECONOMY.
NOT TOO HOT OR TOO COLD.
MAYBE THAT BORES YOU
I DON'T CARE
THAT IS NOT WHAT I'M ABOUT
THIS ECONOMY NEEDS TO BREATHE
WITHOUT THE FED HITTING US WITH
ANOTHER CHOKEHOLD OF A RATE HIKE
LIKE THE LAST ONE.
MOST IMPORTANT MOSAIC IS THE
TRANSPORTS
THIS GROUP WAS INCREDIBLY
NEGATIVE
THEY WERE CHILLING
I'M TALKING ABOUT FEDEX, THE
LARGEST AND JB HUNT, THE SECOND
LARGEST TRUCKING COMPANY AND
FRED SMITH THE CEO OF FEDEX
EXPLAINS THE WORLD IS DOWN
TICKING.
IMPACTING ALL BUSINESS AND IT
WAS A DOWN BEAT CONVERSATION
AFTER A SUBDUED CONFERENCE CALL.
AND THEN IT WAS SOMETHING TO
HEAR THIS MAJOR TRUCKING COMPANY
SAY THERE IS NO PICKUP IN THE
ECONOMY AT ALL
ALL OF THE VOLUME NUMBERS WERE
DOWN 6% TO 7% INCLUDING MARCH SO
WE'RE GOING INTO APRIL COLD.
HOWEVER, YOU COULD NEVER REALLY
RELY ON JUST ONE OR TWO
COMPANIES.
THAT IS TWO ANECDOTAL.
AFTER SAUL THEY HAVE -- CHINA IS
EXPERIENCING A SLOW DOWN UNTIL
ABOUT SEVEN WEEKS AGO BUT THEY
THEY PLACED A BET ON EUROPE.
NOTHING TO DO WITH THE UNITED
STATES
THEY ARE NOT ONE IN THE SAME
THAT IS WHY I WAS SO FOCUSED ON
CSX.
THE RAILROAD SUPPORT
AND I WAS AMAZED AT HOW STRONG
IT WAS AND THAT IS WHY IT HIT A
ALL HEIM HIGH UP 7%.
AND THE BUSINESS DOESN'T STRETCH
OVERSEAS
NO TRAINS GO THERE BUT IT IS A
TESA
TERRIFIC TELL FOR THE ECONOMY
AND ON THE HUNT FOR NEW STOCK
PICKS.
HOW DO YOU DO IT
YOU TURN TO A PAGE THAT ALL
RAILS HAVE IN THE SLIDESHOW
DECK
THIS IS THE REVENUE HIGHLIGHTS
THE FIRST PAGE OF A RAIL IF YOU
WANT TO UNDERSTAND THE ECONOMY
OKAY
THIS TELLS US ABOUT THE ECONOMY.
ANYWAY, IT IS LABELLED STRONG
PRICE AND FAVORABLE MIX DROVE
REVENUE GAINS.
SO THAT IS WHAT IT WOULD SAY
ABOVE THAT
FIRST ONE, CHEMICALS
PLUS FIVE.
COMMENTARY AND THEY INCREASED
BROAD BASED GROWTH OFFSET BY LPG
AND SHIPMENT DECLINES.
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE
WHO COULD MATCH THAT
AND DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE
DECLINE, THAT IS A -- RELATED TO
FRACKING SAND NOT NEEDED FROM
ONE PLACE TO ANOTHER
BUT THE ONE THAT WORKS FOR THIS
IS THE NEW DOW CHEMICAL.
AND THAT'S THE ONE THAT SUPPORTS
A MAGNIFICENT 4.79% YIELD AND
DOW HAS A ROBUST BOOK OF
BUSINESS AS WE KNOW FROM THE
INTERVIEW WITH THE CEO FROM
"SQUAWK ON THE STREET.
THEY HAVE A PLENTY OF PLANTS IN
THE CSX TERRITORY AND SO YOU
PLAY THIS CHEMICALS WITH DOW
AND THEN NEXT AUTOMOTIVE
IT IS DRIVEN BY STRENGTH IN
TRUCKS AND SUVs.
AND GM AND FORD COME TO MINDFUL
I WOULD GO RATHER GO WITH FORD
AND THEY SELL FOR JUST EIGHT
TIMES EARNINGS AND STOM IS MORE
THAN 6% AND THEY CUT COSTS
THIS IS GUTSY AND I'M MAKING IT
HERE, BUY FORD MOTOR AT $9.50.
THEN THERE IS AG AND FOOD UP
12%.
CSX SAID THERE WAS DRIVEN BY
STRENGTH IN ETHANOL.
FORGET THAT.
I'LL GO BACK TO THE WELL
DuPONT IS THE WAY TO PLAY IT
WITH THE MASSIVE PROTECTION
BUSINESS AND GENETICALLY
MODIFIED BUSINESS AND DuPONT HAD
CORN SEEDS AND THAT IS ETHANOL
AND IT ANNOUNCED A WEAK COURT SO
IT IS DERISK SO FOR THAT ONE,
DuPONT
AND HOW ABOUT FOREST, CSX SAID
IT WAS LED BY GROWTH AND
BUILDING AND STRONG IMPORT
DEMAND
TOUGH ONE.
OPEN THE FILE ON WAREHOUSER AND
LOSING MONEY ON A 5% YIELD AND I
WOULD RATHER BUY A BIG HOME
BUILDER.
LET'S BUY LENNAR IN FLORIDA.
AND THEN CONSTRUCTION AND PAVING
PRODUCTS
CATERPILLAR COULD BE A WINNER.
I LIKE THAT STOCK.
BUT IT IS TOO GLOBAL
AND ROCK STONE COULD WORK BUT
BANK OF AMERICA DOWNGRADED IT
THE OTHER DAY AND WORRISOME.
JIM FISH OF WASTE MANAGEMENT
COMES ON THE SHOW AND OFTEN
COMMENTED THE BEST SOURCE OF
REVENUE IS CONSTRUCTION.
THEY ANNOUNCED THE ACQUISITION
OF THE COMPETITOR AND BUSINESS
IS GOOD AND GETTING BETTER THAT
IS THE ONE TO BUY.
AND I'M TALKING ABOUT METAL AND
EQUIPMENT AND FERTILIZER AND THE
METAL IS DOING WELL BECAUSE
THERE IS STEEL BUT TOO MUCH
COMPETITION AND COAL, NOT ON MY
WATCH.
AND INNER MOBILE THAT IS BACK IN
THE WORLD OF J.B. HUNT AND SOME
GROUPS THAT JUST STINK
FOR EXAMPLE, IF YOU TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHERE TO GET YOUR
MONEY TO BUY THESE, EVERYONE IS
SELLING HEALTH CARE.
THEY ARE OBLITERATED BY A PANIC.
AND DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES ARE
CRACKING DOWN ON HEALTH CARE
COSTS AND MANY OF THEM EMBRACING
SINGLE PAYER BUT IT IS UNLIKELY
THE INDUSTRY WILL GET SLAMMED,
EVEN IF BERNIE SANDERS WINS AND
TAKES THE WHITE HOUSE AND IN A
LANDSLIDE AND PICKS UP SENATE
SEATS, I DON'T THINK HE'LL HAVE
THE NUMBERS TO MAKE MEDICARE FOR
ALL HAPPEN
STILL THERE IS NEW POLITICAL
RISK
PORTFOLIO MANAGERS DON'T LIKE
IT
AND YOU KNOW THE PAIN IS OVER
WHEN ELI LILLY AND REALLY GOOD
COMPANIES HAVE MONEY COMING OUT
AND GOING RIGHT HERE
WHEN YOU SEE THAT MONEY POURING
OUT OF A GROUP IT IS LOOKING FOR
A HOME
THAT HOME WILL HAVE ECONOMIC
SENSITIVITY.
WHO HAS THAT
HOW ABOUT THE RAILS AND YOU'LL
OF THE THINGS THAT THEY MOVE ON
THEM
NOW HERE IS THE BOTTOM LINE.
I'M DOING REAL SHORTHAND AND
TRYING TO GIVE YOU A SNAPSHOT OF
THE KIND OF THINGS I DO.
BUT IT IS THE CRAFT.
IT IS THE CRAFT THAT I PRACTICE
FOR 40 YEARS
THERE ARE PLENTY OF WAYS TO SKIN
THE CAT.
THIS WORKS FOR ME AND IF YOU ARE
A CURIOUS PERSON IT COULD WORK
FOR YOU TOO.
I WANT TO GO TO BARBARA IN MY
HOME STATE OF NEW JERSEY
>> Caller: HI, JIM
I'VE BEEN FOLLOWING AND INVESTED
IN RICK ADO, NASDAQ MELI, IT IS
CENTRAL AND SOUTH AMERICA
LEADING MARKET PLACE MUCH LIKE
AMAZON AND E-BAY, IT IS
EXPENSIVE AND VOLATILE AND MAY
EVENTUALLY PHASE OFF AGAINST
AMAZON
BUT WHO HASN'T --
>> I LIKE IT
I WAS ONE OF THE ORIGINAL
INVESTORS WAY BACK WHEN I COULD
INVEST
I THINK IT IS A SWELL COMPANY.
IT HAS BEEN SWELL AND HAD BETTER
GROWTH THAN E-BAY.
THAT IS A GOOD CALL BY BARBARA
FROM NEW JERSEY.
>>> IF YOU ARE LOOKING FOR
ECONOMIC SENSAIVITY AND PEOPLE
ARE BAILING OUT OF HEALTH CARE,
LOOK TO THE RAIL OPERATORS AND
WHAT THEY MOVE AND PLUS LENNAR
AND FORD AND WASTE MANAGEMENT.
CSX LATEST RESULTS TELL ME THERE
IS MONEY TO BE MADE HERE
ON MAD TONIGHT, ONE OF THE MOST
SCRUTINIZED STOCKS IN THE MARKET
I'M TALKING NETFLIX.
TIME TO ADD THIS STREAMING STAR
TO YOUR CUE OR DID YOU MISS THE
MOST IMPORTANT PART OF THE MOVIE
AND STILL WAITING FOR IT TO GET
BACK
AND DAN LOWE MAY STIR A POT WHEN
IT COMES TO CAMPBELL'S SOUP BUT
IS THE PROXY BATTLE SIMMERING
AND STILL TOO HOT TO CONSIDER OR
ALL OVER AND THEY ARE ALL
TOGETHER IN ONE CAN.
AND WHAT IS ON THE HORIZON FOR
FIRST VERIZON, I HAVE THE CEO.
SO STAY WITH CRAMER.
>> Announcer: DON'T MISS A
SECOND OF "MAD MONEY."
FOLLOW AT JIM CRAMER ON TWITTER.
HAVE A QUESTION, TWEET CRAMER AT
#MADTWEETS
OR GIVE US A CALL AT
800-743-CNBC
MISS SOMETNGHI IN HEAD TO "MAD
MONEY".CNBC.COM.
♪ ♪
Creating the perfect night...
Just takes a little creativity.
The light beer you've been
waiting for has arrived.
Lower carbs.
Lower calories.
Higher expectations.
Corona Premier.
♪ When you have nausea, ♪
♪ heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, ♪
♪ upset stomach, ♪
♪ diarrhea... ♪
Girl, Pepto ultra coating will
treat your stomach right.
♪Nausea, heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, upset stomach,♪
♪ diarrhea... ♪
Try Pepto with Ultra coating.
Breathe freely fast, with Vicks
Sinex.
My congestion's gone.
I can breathe again! Ahhhh!
I can breathe again! Ughh!
Vicks Sinex.
Breathe On.
>>> CAN NETFLIX PEACEFULLY
COEXIST WITH THE NEW STREAMING
SERVICE?
WILL PEOPLE PAY $15.99 FOR A
SUBSCRIPTION ON TOP OF $6.99 FOR
DISNEY AND 11.99 FOR THE YOUTUBE
PREMIUM.
IF YOU LISTEN TO NETFLIX
CONFERENCE CALL I THINK THE
ANSWER IS A RESOUNDING YES
WHY?
BECAUSE I REALIZED HOW MUCH
CONTENT I'VE MISSED OUT ON SINCE
THE LAST CALL THREE MONTHS AGO
AND WHAT WAS I THINKING MISSING
TRIPLE FRONTIER, A BEN AFFLECK
MOVING SEEN BY 52 MILLION
HOUSEHOLDS AND MY LOVED IT WITH
45 MILLION OTHERS NOW I HAVE TO
SEE IT NOW
IF YOU LOVE KINGDOM AND THE
PIECE WITH ZOMBIES, AND I DID
WATCH FIRE THE GREAT OF THE
PARTY THAT NEVER HAPPENED SO AT
LEAST I HAD SOMETHING TO TALK
ABOUT AND I MILKED THAT FOR
WEEKS ON END
FIRE FEST AND I EVEN WATCHED IT
ON THE OTHER GUY'S SHOW.
AND NETFLIX IS ABOUT GIVING YOU
SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT.
SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT WHEN YOU
COME IN ON MONDAY MORNING.
THAT IS WHAT IT IS
IT IS ABOUT NOT FEELING LIKE A
SMOOTH WHEN -- A STOOGE WHEN
EVERYBODY ELSE IS WATCHING BIRD
BOX AND THE REAL METRIC IS CAN
WE KEEP MEMBERS HAPPY WITH THE
IRISHMAN AND JIMMY HOFFA'S
MURDER AND FILMED ON MY STREET
AND IF A FAMILY LIKE SIX WANTS
TO GO TO THE MOVIES, I BREAK OUT
A HUNDRED.
BUT TO WATCH PACHINO AND DENERO
HAVE BOTH APPEARED TOGETHER IN A
SCORE ZEZY MONEY AND MAYBE SOME
CANDY AND YEAH AND IT COST NEXT
TO NOTHING
NETFLIX IS A STEAL
IT IS NOT JUST A BARGAIN, IT IS
WHAT I CALL A NECESSARY BARGAIN.
AN NB.
I DON'T CARE WHAT THEY SAY ABOUT
WEAK DOMESTIC.
I CARE ABOUT THE SLATE OR
MISSING APP OR NOT SEEING THE
IRISHMAN
AS MY SQUAWK ON THE STREAK
CO-HOST SAYS, I HAVE A WHOLE
BUNCH OF HOUSES AND THEY ALL
HAVE CABLE
I HAVE TO HAVE CABLE
I WENT OVER MY BILLS, ONE OF
THEM IS $325 AND ANOTHER $270
AND ANOTHER $225 AND TWO AT
$187
THE HORROR
OF COURSE, SOME OF THAT IS HIGH
SPEED INTERNATIONAL.
BUT FOR THE MOST PART THEY ARE
FOR A HANDFUL OF GAMES AND
HUNDREDS OF CHANNELS THAT I
NEVER WATCH TO HAVE TO GO
THROUGH.
I PAY THEM NOT TO HAVE TO GO
THROUGH THEM
I MEAN HUNDREDS OF THEM.
THERE ARE LITERALLY HUNDREDS OF
CHANNELS THAT YOU DON'T WATCH
EITHER.   I KNOW YOU
AND THAT IS OKAY
I DON'T THINK THE PRICES WONDER
HOW COULD I GET THIS DOWN.
AND NETFLIX IS RAISING PRICES BY
A COUPLE OF BUCKS AND SAY, WOW,
WHAT A BARGAIN
A NECESSARY BARGAIN.
NB
YOU CAN'T SAY THAT ABOUT MANY
CABLE NETWORKS EXCEPT FOR CNBC
WHEN IT WAS CREATED YEARS AGO
TODAY.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
AND I HAVE NO DESIRE TO WATCH 85
OF THEM.
AND WITH NETFLIX I'M DESPERATE
TO WATCH EVERYTHING.
EVERYTHING THEY HAVE
DISNEY, WHEN MY KIDS WERE
YOUNGER.
I DID TAKE ESPN PLUS FOR $4.99
AND NOT THE BARGAIN IT YOU WANT
TO WIN IN FANTASY FOOTBALL WHICH
I ALMOST ALWAYS DO
MY WIFE LOVES HULU SO SHE WOULD
WATCH WHERE SHE WANTS AND SHE
PLAYS THAT CANDY CRUSH
WHAT IS THAT ABOUT
IT TAKES YOUR CORTEX -- I BET
APPLE STREAMING SERVICE WILL BE
LIKE THAT TOO.
I DON'T RECALL ANYONE ASKING ME
ABOUT ANYTHING ON YOUTUBE BUT I
WISH I HAD WATCHED THAT "GAME OF
THRONES.
I DON'T KNOW IF I SHOULD CANCEL
HBO UNTIL MY WIFE STOPS WATCHING
IT
$15 A MONTH.
NOT MUCH OF A SAVING
IN THE END NETFLIX IS CHARGING
$15.99 AND CABLE NETWORKS COULD
CHARGE MORE FOR WHAT I WANT AND
IT IS A HUNDRED DOLLARS PLUS
CANDY THAT I'LL NEVER TALK
ABOUT.
THAT IS WHY MY TWO MILLENNIAL
KIDS ONLY TAKE NETFLIX AND THINK
MOVIES AND CABLE ARE RIPOFFS AND
DON'T KNOW THAT I HAVE A SHOW.
YOU HAVE TO FIND A WAY TO GIVE
ME SPORTS PACKAGES WITHOUT THE
85 CHANNELS FROM ONE TO 100 AND
I COULD BE A CORD CUTTER AFTER
SEEING THE CABLE BILLS
THEY ARE NECESSARY
AND I WOULD SAY THE SHOWS ARE
EITHER NECESSARY OR NOR A
BARGAIN.
BUT THE CABLE, WHEN IT COMES TO
CABLE, I SURE DO LIKE THEIR
STOCKS
MAKE A LOT OF MONEY.
MUCH MORE "MAD MONEY" AHEAD. IT
WAS A FOOD FIGHT WITH CAMPBELLS
AND DAN LOBE OPENS UP A SPICY
CAN OF A PROXY BATTLE.
AND I'LL GIVE YOU MY TAKE.
AND I'LL TALK TO FIRST HORIZON
AND AFTER CHEVRON COULD OTHER
OIL STOCKS GET ON THE ACTION
I'M EYEING THE MERGER AND
ACQUISITION IN THE OIL PATCH SO
STAY WITH CRAMER
You might take something
for your heart...
your joints...
or your digestion...
so why wouldn't you
take something
for the most important
part of you...
your brain.
With an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish,
Prevagen has been shown
in clinical trials
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
>>> SOMETHING YOU OFTEN ASK ME
ON TWITTER, HOW DO YOU KNOW WHEN
YOU ARE DEALING WITH A REAL COME
BACK IN A ONCE BEATEN DOWN STOCK
AS TO OPPOSED TO A FLASH IN THE
PAN THAT COULD VANISH UNDER YOUR
FEET
AND THAT IS THE QUESTION WE NEED
TO ASK ABOUT
AN ICONIC NAME TO DREDGE UP
HERE, CAMPBELL'S SOUP.
THE CAMPBELLS PORK AND BEANS
THAT IS WHERE THE SYMBOL COMES
FROM
AND YOU KNOW FROM THE NAMESAKE
V-8 AND SWAN SON BROTH AND THE
BRAND.
HERE IS A COMPANY AN ABSOLUTE
MESS
WE KNOW THAT THE PANTRY PLACE
BROUGHT IN -- BOUGHT IN THE
CENTER OF THE AISLE HAVE BEEN
STRUGGLING FOR YEARS AS YOUNGER
PEOPLE LIKE THE STOCK THAT -- A
FRENCH ONION SOUP.
THINK IT IS FROM WHEN -- THIS IS
LAFAYETTE.
AND CAMPBELL'S SOUP STRUGGLING
MORE THAN MOST
IT WAS LAST YEAR THAT DENISE
MORRIS LEFT THE COMPANY AND
LEAVING THE NUMBER IN DISARRAY
AND THE BUSINESS SEEMED
RUDDERLESS AND THEN TWO THINGS
HAPPENED
THE INTERIM MANAGEMENT ANNOUNCED
A STRATEGIC REVIEW TELLING US
THEY WERE PUTTING ALL OPTION ON
THE TABLE AND IN AUGUST IT
BECAME AN IF ACTIVIST STORY.
ONE OF THE MOST FAMOUS TAKEOVER
ARTICTS OR ACTIVISTS, DAN LOBE,
THE HEAD OF THIRD POINT, DECIDED
TO GET INVOLVED AND ALMOST
IMMEDIATELY DECLARED WAR ON THE
BOARD OF DIRECTORS
HE DOESN'T LIE -- DOESN'T BUY A
LOT OF COMPANIES
HE RECOGNIZE TAD CAMPBELL AS
SOUP HAS BEEN AN UNDERMANAGED
MESS WHICH IS RIGHT OUT OF THE
GATE HE ASKED THEM TO PUT IT UP
FOR SALE
THE ACTIVISTS STOCK AND THE
STORY HAS MOVING PARTS
WE KNOW LOBE HAS A PLAN.
BUT IS IT A GOOD PLAN?
CAN HE CON VIBS THE BOARD OF
DIRECTORS TO FOLLOW THE BRAND OR
GO OVER THEIR HEADS AND APPEAL
DIRECTLY TO THE SHAREHOLDERS AND
IF IT IS A PROXY FIGHT, CAN HE
ACTUALLY WIN OR IS THE CURRENT
LEADERSHIP HAVE TOO MUCH
ENTRENCHED SUPPORT
IN THIS CASE FROM THE FAMILY
THAT OWNS NEARLY HALF OF THE
COMPANY AND THEN THE MANAGEMENT.
THEY TRY TO STRIKE A COMPROMISE.
WILL THEY FIGHT THE INCURSION BY
WORKING HARDER TO MAKE THE
SHAREHOLDERS HAPPY
THERE ARE A DOZEN POTENTIAL
PERMEATIONS FOR CAMPBELL'S SOUP
WHICH IS WHY WE'RE WAITING FOR
THE SMOKE TO CLEAR BEFORE
DIGGING DEEPER
AND MAYBE THAT IS A MISTAKE.
AFTER BEING CLOBBERED, THEY HAD
A COME BACK AND UP 9% AND AS THE
BOARD OF DIRECTORS BROUGHT IN A
TALENTED NEW CEO AND THE LAST
COUPLE OF QUARTERS WERE BETTER
THAN MANY FEARS AN THE PACKAGE
FOOD SPACE, SUDDENLY OUT OF
NOWHERE HAS WIND ON ITS BACK
AFTER GENERAL MILLS REPORTED A
GOOD QUARTER AND PEPSICO THIS
MORNING AND THE BENCHMARK AT
2.59 THE DIVIDENDS LOOK MORE
ATTRACTIVE
EVEN AT 3.55% YIELD.
SO THEY ARE PAYING YOU TO WAIT
FOR A TURN
SO HOW DID THEY DO IT?
AND IS THE TURN IN THE STOCK FOR
REAL
FIRST YOU NEED TO UNDERSTAND
WHERE CAMPBELL'S STOCK AND THE
COMPANY IS COMING FROM
AFTER MAKING A SERIES OF SMALL
ACQUISITIONS, THE COMPANY SWUNG
FOR THE FENCES SNAPPING UP
SNYDER LANCE FOR $6.1 BILLION.
DRAMATIC OVERPAY
WHEN YOU THINK OF IT, THINK OF
SNYDER'S PRETZELS OR POP SECRET
OWNED BY GENERAL MILLS AND MY
PERSONAL FAVORITE NIP CHEESE
NIP CHEESE
THEY'RE REALLY GOOD FOR YOU.
THEY'RE ORANGE
THE TRANSACTION CLOSED ROUGHLY A
YEAR AGO AND RIGHT OUT OF THE
GATE THERE WERE PROBLEMS
11 MONTHS AGO THEY REPORTED AN
OKAY QUARTER WITH DISMAL I'DEN
AND THEN THE CEO ANNOUNCED HER
SUDDEN RETIREMENT.
THERE WAS NOT MUCH ABOUT THIS
SITUATION THAT INSPIRED
CONFIDENCE
SO IT WAS A SHOCK WHEN DAN LOBE
CAME OUT IN AUGUST AND TOLD US
THAT HIS HEDGE FUND THIRD POINT
HAD TAKEN A 5.6% STAKE IN THE
COMPANY.
LOBE IMMEDIATELY CRITICIZED
MANAGEMENT, ARGUING THAT
CAMPBELL'S DEBT FUEL TAKEOVER
SPREE, REMEMBER I TOLD YOU WHEN
THEY DID THIS ONE, SNYDER'S
LANCE, THIS WAS JUST A KILLER
HOW MUCH DEBT THEY TOOK IN
HE SAID THAT ACQUISITION PUT
THEM IN A PRECARIOUS SPACE
AND NO KIDDING
$6.1 BILLION WORTH OF DEBT
FOR SOMETHING THAT REALLY WAS
NOT THAT -- NO BLUE CHIP
HOW ABOUT THAT
HE POINTED OUT THE STOCK WAS
BASICALLY FLAT SINCE 1996, OKAY.
THAT IS ABOUT IT
AND HE REALLY HAMMERED HOME LACK
OF LEADERSHIP SAYING THE CURRENT
CEO VACUUM REMINDS US OF
BENJAMIN FRANKLIN'S RES ONAT
INSIGHT IF YOU FAIL TO PLAN, YOU
ARE PLANNING TO FAIL
BUT THE CEO STARTED A STRATEGIC
REVIEW AND LOBE SAID THE OME
OUTCOME IS TO SELL ITSELF
THROUGH STRATEGIC FIRE
THAT'S TYPICAL ACTIVIST TALK
WE CAN'T FIX IT SO JUST SELL IT.
BUT THAT IS ALWAYS AN UPHILL
BATTLE
BECAUSE YOU SEE CAMPBELL'S SOUP
IS STILL A FAMILY BUSINESS
A LITTLE HISTORY
ABOUT 122 YEARS AGO A CHEMIST
NAMED JOHN T. DURANCE INVESTED
CONDENSED SOUP AND WENT ON TO
RUN THE COMPANY AND BUY UP A
CONTROLLING INTEREST
THIS IS CONDENSED.
YOU PUT A LOT OF TOMATOES IN
THIS
HE FIGURED OUT HOW TO DO IT.
TODAY HIS DESCENDANTS OWN 45%
AND THEY DON'T WANT TO SELL AND
THEY DON'T CARE ABOUT CAPITAL
APPRECIATION, THEY MAINLY JUST
WENT THE DIVIDENDS
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SHOULD WE JUST KEEP DOING IT
UNTIL IT FALLS
CREAM OF CELERY, IT IS MY FAVE
AND DO YOU THINK THERE IS ANY
CELERY IN THIS
SHOW OF HANDS?
THANK YOU.
LOBE GOT INVOLVED AND THE
COMPANY AND THEN AT THE END OF
AUGUST, THE NUMBERS WERE
WORRISOME BUT THE GROSS MARGIN
AFTER THE COST OF GOODS SOLD
DECLINED AND ONCE AGAIN
MANAGEMENT GAVE AWFUL GUIDANCE
HOME MADE STYLE CHICKEN NOODLE
ANY CHICKEN IN THIS?
RICHARD.
AT
AT THE SAME TIME, THE COMPANY
SAID THEY WOULD SELL CAMPBELL
INTERNATIONAL AND THE KELSON
GROUP AND THE MANUFACTURING
OPERATIONS IN ASIA AND CAMPBELL
FRESH.
WHEN THEY BOUGHT THIS THEY CAME
ON THE SHOW AND STARTED USING IT
AND I USE THEIR SALAD DRESSINGS
CONSTANTLY
THEY'RE ALL UP TOP IN THE -- IN
THE FRIG SECTION WHY YOU MAYBE
USE WISH BONE.
AND A WAY, THEY HAD THIS GARDEN
FRESH GOURMET AND THAT CUSHIONED
THE BLOW FROM THE LOUSY
GUIDANCE
AT THE BEGINNING -- THIS IS
GOOD
I'VE HAD THIS.
I'M NOT KIDDING.
AT THE BEGINNING OF OCTOBER, DAN
LOBE OFFICIALLY WANTS A PROXY
FIGHT TO REPLACE THE ENTIRE
BOARD OF DIRECTORS AND -- THE
ENTIRE BOARD
AND EVEN RECRUITED A DEFECTOR
FROM THE DURANT FAMILY WHO IS
UNHAPPY WITH THE DIRECTION OF
THE BUSINESS
AS DISPUTE WENT ON, THE DISPUTE
GOT MORE AND MORE VICIOUS.
BUT BEFORE IT GOT TOO HEATED AND
EVERYTHING BLEW UP
LOBE AND THE BOARD OF DIRECTORS
MADE A DEAL AT THE END OF
NOVEMBER, IT WAS SMART
THREE DAYS BEFORE THE ANNUAL
MEETING LOBE GETS TWO BOARD
SEATS WITH INPUT INTO THE NEW
CEO.
AND THE STORY BECAME DIFFERENT
AND THE ACTIVISTS AND BOARD WERE
WORKING TOGETHER AND MADE THIS
BRILLIANT HIRE, THIS GUY NAMED
MARK CLOUS, JOINING THE COMPANY,
THAT SOLD PINNACLE TO PIN AGRA
AND IT IS COME BACK WITH A
VENGEANCE IN 2019 SO THAT IS
SELF HELP.
AND NOW LOOKING CLOSE TO SELLING
THE COOKIE BUSINESS TO MONGA
LEASE TO MAKE US ALL FAT
THEY ARE GETTING $510 MILLION
FOR BULL HOUSE WHICH THEY PAID A
LOT MORE FOR AND THIS COULD BE
THE TIP OF THE ICEBERG LETTUCE
THAT I USED THIS ON.
PLUS WHEN CAMPBELL'S SOUP
REPORTED THE LATEST NUMBERS AT
THE END OF THE FEBRUARY, THEY
CAME IN BETTER THAN EXPECTED
MARK CLOUS MADE IT CLEAR HE'S
MAKING REAL PROGRESS,
STABILIZING THE CORE BUSINESS.
WHICH IS TRUE.
THAT SAID I THINK SOME OF THE
REASON THIS HAS TO DO WITH A
SENSE OF OPTIMISM ABOUT THE DAN
LOBE INVOLVEMENT NOW THAT HE AND
MANAGEMENT ARE COOPERATING
SO WHAT DO WE DO WITH THIS
STOCK?
THEY BOUGHT EVERY LOUSY, EVERY
BRAND.
THEY JUST BOUGHT EVERYTHING AND
THEY BOUGHT -- REMEMBER THIS ONE
FROM THE GUY WHO LIKE -- WELL I
CAN'T SAY WHAT HE DID TO THE
COMPANY.
AND THIS -- REMEMBER THIS.
AND HERE IS THE BOTTOM LINE.
AFTER SPENDING YEARS LOST IN THE
WILDERNESS AND BUYING UP
COMPANIES THAT NOBODY WANTED,
CAMPBELL'S SOUP IS FINALLY
TURNING ITSELF AROUND.
BUT WITH THE STOCK NOW TRADING
AT 15.7 TIMES NEXT YEAR'S
EARNING ESTIMATES I'M NOT SURE
HOW MUCH UPSIDE IT HAS LEFT IF
LOBE CAN'T FIND A WAY TO
ENGINEER A SALE.
THE DEBT IS STACKED AGAINST THAT
OUTCOME TO BEGIN WITH BUT THINGS
GO SOUTH, I THINK THAT COULD
MAKE A SALE A GENUINE
POSSIBILITY INCLUDING CLOUS'S
SUCCESSFUL OF PINNACLE AND WITH
THE DIVIDEND TO WAIT FOR THE
FAMILY TO LOSE THE RESOLVE TO
STAY INDEPENDENT
LET ME TAKE A QUESTION
LET'S GO TO -- LET'S GO TO
DENNIS IN CALIFORNIA
DENNIS
>> Caller: B-B-B BOO-YAH JIM
I'M A FIRST TIME CALLER AND I
LIKE YOUR SHOW SO I'M THINKING
ABOUT ADDING TO MY POSITION IN
COSTCO
SO I HAVE SOME RESEARCH AND I
COME UP FROM $200 IN THE YEAR TO
THE CURRENT PRICE OF $245.
I ALSO THINK IT HAS TWO COUNTS
GOING FORWARD.
ONE IS THE SPECIAL DIVIDEND
WHICH IT PAID IN 20 -- MAY OF
2015 AND 2017.
>> RIGHT
>> YEAH.
>> Caller: AND THE OTHER
CATALYST IS THE INCREASED STORE
TRAFFIC BY HIGHER GAS PRICES AND
PEOPLE FUEL UP AND THEN DO YOUR
COSTCO RUN
SO DO YOU THINK AT THIS LEVEL IT
IS A ACCIDENT RISK ON TRADE.
>> IT IS ONLY TWO POINTS OFT
HIGH
YOU CAN'T BUY THIS ALL AT ONCE
THIS IS A STOCK WHERE YOU BUY
SOME TOMORROW, AND THEN YOU BUY
SOME ON A TRRETREAT.
BECAUSE YOU COME IN AND BUY SOME
AND THEN BOOM THE MARKET GOES
DOWN AND YOU DON'T HAVE ANY FIRE
POWERMENT BUT THE CONCEPTION OF
THE IDEA, I'M ALL IN.
>> THERE IS STILL HOPE FOR
STRUGGLING CAMPBELL'S SOUP.
AND WHILE THE FUTURE IS UNCLUR
AND THE FUNDAMENTALS -- LET'S
CALL THEM IMPROVING.
AND IF DAN LOBE CAN CONVINCE IT
TO SELL ITSELF IT COULD GO
HIGHER
AND MUCH MORE "MAD MONEY."
THE FED'S RATE RAISE IS OVER BUT
I'LL TALK TO THE CEO OF A
COMPANY AND.
THEN DID CHEVRON ADD ENERGY
THROUGH A PATCH AND I'M LOOKING
FOR OTHER PLAYERS THAT COULD BE
M&A BUYERS AND THEN TONIGHT'S
RAPID EDITION OF "THE LIGHTNING
ROUND.
I consulted with your
grandmother's doctor.
We can do the
screening at her house.
Hi.
This is the man that's going
to check your eyes grandma.
Cognizant AI solutions
are helping healthcare companies
advance diagnostics
and prevent blindness
in patients with diabetes.
Everything looks good.
You have beautiful eyes.
♪♪
>>> WE SPEND A LOT OF TIME
FOCUSING ON THE MAJOR NATIONAL
BANKS AND THEY ARE DOING WELL
BUT TAKE FIRST HORIZON, A
TENNESSEE-BASED BANK WITH 300
BRANCHES ACROSS THE SOUTHEAST.
YESTERDAY MORNING THIS REGION
REPORTED A STRONG QUARTER,
INLINE EARNINGS AND HIGHER THAN
EXPECTED SALES AND THE STOCK
VAULTED 3% AND ANOTHER 1.6%
TODAY BUT EVEN AFTER THE MOVE,
FIRST HORIZON IS CHEAP
SELLING FOR TEN TIMES THIS
YEAR'S EARNING AT 1.6 TIMES THE
BOOK VALUE
WHAT WOULD IT BE WORTH IF THE
PLACE IS CLOSED.
IF IT LIQUIDATED
SO COULD THIS STOCK HAVE MUCH
MORE ROOM TO RUN
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT BRIAN
JORDAN
THE CHAIRMAN ABOUT WHERE THE
COMPANY IS HEADING
WELCOME BACK TO "MAD MONEY."
>> THANK YOU
IT IS GOOD TO BE BACK.
>> BRIAN, IF YOU WERE TO TELL ME
THAT THERE WAS A BANK THAT HAD
7% LOAN GROWTH AND OVER 10%
CUSTOMER DEPOSIT GROWTH AND ONLY
$5 MILLION IN CHARGEOFFS, I
WOULD TELL YOU THAT IS ABOUT AN
18 PRICE SERIES MULTIPLE AND
SHOULD BE ABOUT 25
CAN YOU PLEASE EXPLAIN TO ME
WHAT IS HAPPENING IN THIS
COUNTRY YOU HAVE THE BEST
QUARTER I'VE SEEN AND -- PEOPLE
SAY, OH, THAT IS OKAY.
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
>> YEAH, WE HAVE -- WE DID HAVE
A VERY GOOD QUARTER.
WE HAVE AN INTERESTING
ENVIRONMENT.
I THINK AT THIS POINT THERE IS
STILL A FAIR AMOUNT OF QUESTION
ABOUT WHETHER THIS ECONOMY IS
GOING TO DIE OF OLD AGE AND WHAT
THAT MEANS FOR THE FINANCIAL
INSTITUTIONS STOCKS.
AND IN OUR CASE WE, AS YOU KNOW,
HAD AN INTEGRATION LAST YEAR
THAT TOOK A FAIR AMOUNT OF TIME.
BUT I THINK WHAT WE'VE PROVEN
OUT OVER THE LAST HALF OF 2018
AND FIRST QUARTER OF 2019 AND I
THINK WE'LL CONTINUE INTO THE
SECOND QUARTER IS WE'RE BUILDING
MOMENTUM
AND WE'RE SEEING GREAT PROGRESS
ON THE BANK WE INTEGRATED, THE
ECONOMY IS STILL GOOD.
AND WE'RE SEEING GOOD LOAN
DEMAND, AND GOOD CUSTOMER
DEPOSIT ACTIVITY
WE'RE VERY EXCITED ABOUT HOW
WE'RE POSITIONED.
>> SEE WHAT I'M HOPING IS THAT
AT A CERTAIN POINT AND WE WON'T
FOCUS ON NET INTEREST INCOME OR
MARGIN AND A SMALL AMOUNT OF
BASIS POINTS BUT REAL GROWTH
AND I SEE WHEN I LOOK AT YOUR
SOUTH FLORIDA PROPERTIES OR
HOUSTON OR THE CAROLINAS, YOU
HAVE GENUINE GROWTH LIKE A
GROWTH COMPANY THAT WE WOULD
CHERISH NOT AS A INTEREST RATE
PLAY BUT AS A COMPANY THAT IS
GOING TO PUT UP MAYBE
DOUBLE-DIGIT NUMBERS
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
I THINK THAT IS ONE OF THE
UNIQUE FEATURES OF OUR
ORGANIZATION
TENNESSEE WHERE WE'VE BEEN FOR
155 YEARS IS A GREAT MARKET AND
GREAT GROWTH DYNAMIC
WE EXPANDED WITH TOE HOLDS
THROUGH CAPITAL BANK INTO NORTH
CAROLINA, SOUTH CAROLINA
AND WE HAVE AN 8-YEAR-OLD
PRESENCE OR SO IN HOUSTON,
TEXAS.
SO WE'VE GOT A TOE HOLD IN
STRONG GROWTH MARKETS AND WE SEE
A TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF
OPPORTUNITY TO WIN AND GAIN
SHARE AND TO BUILD THE BUSINESS
AND AS I SET EARLIER, BUILD THE
MOMENTUM.
>> ARE THERE PROPERTIES FOR
SALE
BECAUSE YESTERDAY WE SPOKE WITH
ANNA BOUGHTIN, CHAIRMAN OF SEND
AIR.
SHE'S GREAT.
AND SHE WANTS TO EXPAND
EVERYWHERE AND I'M THINKING
YOU'RE IN SOUTH FLORIDA, ARE
THERE BANKS STILL FOR SALE IN
SOUTH FLORIDA THAT YOU COULD
BUY?
>> I THINK THERE ARE PROBABLY
ARE REGULAR WAY TRANSACTIONS
THAT COULD GET DONE.
I THINK THE MARKET HAS PROBABLY
SHIFTED WITH THE ANNOUNCEMENT OF
BB&T AND SUN TRUST AND I THINK
THE TRANSACTIONS WILL BE LARGER
AND I SAID WE'RE FOCUSED ON
EXECUTION IN 2019 AND 2020 AND
BEYOND
WE'RE NOT REALLY IN THE FRAME OF
MIND WHERE WE'RE THINKING ABOUT
ACQUISITION.
WE WANT TO CAPITALIZE ON WHAT
WE'VE GOT IN TERMS OF FOOT HOLD
IN NORTH CAROLINA, SOUTH
CAROLINA, SOUTH FLORIDA AND
BUILD MOMENTUM WITH THAT FOR THE
SHORT-TERM
>> NOW A LOT OF PEOPLE MIGHT BE
SAYING, LOOK, HE ONLY HAS
$5 MILLION IN CHARGEOFFS BECAUSE
NOBODY IS GETTING A LOAN WHO IS
EVEN AT ALL RISKY.
I THINK THAT THERE IS A NEW
ATTITUDE POST 2008 AND '09 BUT
YOU HAVE A LOT OF DEBTORS OR
PEOPLE WHO WANT MONEY THAT WOULD
BE GOOD CREDIT BUT NOT SUPER
IT IS NOT LIKE YOU ARE NOT
TAKING ANY RISK, IS IT
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
WE HAVE A VERY NICE -- A
GRANULAR PORTFOLIO
IT IS GEOGRAPHICALLY DIVERSE
IT IS A STRONG PORTFOLIO
IT IS LARGELY A COMMERCIAL AND
INDUSTRIAL LENDING PORTFOLIO SO
IT IS COMMERCIAL ENTITIES AND
REAL ESTATE AND THEN CONSUMER.
I THINK RISK IS BEING MANAGED
BETTER TODAY IN THE FINANCIAL
SERVICES INDUSTRY THAN IT WAS
PRE-2008, 2009
BUT THERE IS STILL A LOT OF
COMPETITION FOR EVERY DEAL THAT
IS OUT THERE
THE PRICING AND THE STRUCTURE IS
STILL VERY GOOD FOR BORROWERS
AND I THINK IT IS STILL SOUND
FOR THE FINANCIAL SERVICES
INDUSTRY
BUT I THINK WE'RE TAKING
MEASURED AND BETTER RISK TODAY
I THINK OUR PORTFOLIO TO THE
EXTENT THAT IT EVER DOES SEE A
DOWNTURN IN THE ECONOMY, WILL BE
PESSIMISTIC AND SAY WHEN, I
THINK OUR PORTFOLIO WILL PERFORM
VERY WELL.
WE'VE DONE A TREMENDOUS AMOUNT
OF WORK OVER TEN YEARS TO CHANGE
OUR CREDIT PROFILE TO THIS
GRANULAR AND DIVERSIFIED CNI
ORIENTED PORTFOLIO WHICH I THINK
WILL HOLD UP AND PERFORM VERY,
VERY WELL THROUGHOUT A CHANGE IN
ECONOMY.
>> SO HOW MUCH OF WHAT YOU SAID
IS CHANGED HAS TO DO WITH THE
10% OF THE REVENUES THAT YOU
SPENT ON TECHNOLOGY OR IS THAT
MORE CUSTOMER FACING, NOT
NECESSARILY A WAY TO BE ABLE TO
MEASURE RISK
>> YEAH, I THINK IT IS A LITTLE
BIT OF BOTH.
THE TECHNOLOGY SPEND IN THE
INDUSTRY IS PROBABLY THE
FASTEST-GROWING THING IN THE
BUSINESS
AND I THINK THE COST PRESSURES
ON THE TECHNOLOGY SIDE WILL GO
UP
IT WILL BE A LITTLE BIT OF BOTH.
IT WILL BE BACK OFFICE AND TOOLS
TO HELP YOU DECISION CREDIT AND
ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE AND
TOOLS OF THAT NATURE AND THE
CUSTOMER-FACING TECHNOLOGIES
THINGS LIKE REAL-TIME PAYMENTS,
VENMO, ZEL, TECHNOLOGIES THAT
ALLOW YOU TO PROVIDE DIFFERENT
TOOLS AND FEATURES THAT ALLOW
CUSTOMERS TO DO A BETTER JOB OF
BANKING.
HOW THEY WANT TO BANK AND WHEN
THEY WANT TO BANK.
AND WITH A TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF
FLEXIBILITY.
SO WE'LL HAVE AN INCREASING
PRESSURE ON THE TECHNOLOGY SPEND
OVER TIME AND YOU MAY HAVE NOTED
THAT WE SPENT A FAIR AMOUNT OF
TIME TALKING ABOUT HOW WE'RE
TRYING TO PAY FOR THAT WITH OUR
EXISTING COST BASE SO WE'RE
REORIENTED THE CALL STRUCTURE TO
ENABLE US TO MAKE THE
INVESTMENTS.
>> ONE LAST QUESTION AND IT HAS
TO BE QUICK.
NEXT MOVE BY THE FED, RATE CUT
OR RATE HIKE
>> IF I HAD TO GUESS, I WOULD
SAY IT IS FLAT FOR A WHILE AND
THEN DOWN.
>> WOW
>> OKAY.
WE'LL END IT THERE
THANK YOU TO BRYAN JORDAN FROM
CHAIRMAN AND CEO
THIS IS AN INEXPENSIVE GROWTH
STOCK.
"MAD MONEY" IS BACK AFTER THE
BREAK.
>>> IT IS TIME -- IT IS -- AND
THEN "THE LIGHTNING ROUND" IS
OVER
ARE YOU READY?
I'M WITH JULIA
>> Caller: HEY, JIM.
THANKS FOR TAKING MY CALL.
>> OF COURSE.
>> Caller: MY QUESTION IS ON A
RISK NETWORK, I WAS WONDERING, I
HAD IT, MADE A NICE PROFIT AND
SOLD IT AND I'M WONDERING IF I
SHOULD GET BACK INTO IT.
>> I THINK THE GREAT MANAGER AND
WOULD BUY IT AT A 52-WEEK HIGH
AND NOT RELATIVE BUT A HIGH
STOCK AND THE STOCK WILL COME
DOWN AND I WOULD BUY IT IN TWO
DAYS
I WOULD NOT BUY IT RIGHT NOW
LET'S GO TO SKIP IN CALIFORNIA
SKIP
>> Caller: JIM, HOW ARE YOU
DOING?
>> I'M DOING WELL, SKIP, HOW
ABOUT YOU.
>> Caller: I'M GOOD.
MY QUESTION IS ON NVIDIA.
>> WE SOLD IT AT HIGH 200 AND
BOUGHT IT BACK FOR THE CLUB.
BECAUSE WE JUST THINK IT HAS --
WE LOVE THE MEL AN OX
ACQUISITION SO I'LL SAY BUY BUY
BUY.
>> AND TO MARTY IN NEW YORK.
GO AHEAD.
>> Caller: HI.
>> HI.
HI
>> Caller: HI.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
HI
>> HI.
>> Caller: HI.
>> MARTY
IT IS JIM.
YOU'RE ON.
HI
>> Caller: HI.
CONSULTATION STOCKS AND I WAS
WONDERING IF IT IS A BUY OR A
SELL OR HOLD IT.
>> CONSTELLATION BRANDS, A
COMPANY THEY OWN HALF OF CANOPY
GROWTH IS MERGING WITH ACREAGE
I THINK THEY'RE CANNABIS IS
GOOD
AND I THINK THE BEER BUSINESS IS
OKAY
LET'S GO TO CHRIS IN MICHIGAN.
CHRIS?
>> Caller: BOO-YAH, JIM.
>> BOO-YAH.
>> Caller: ON BOSH HEALTH
COMPANY.
I BOUGHT IT THIS LAST FALL AND
HEALTH CARE INDUSTRY STOCKS ARE
DOWN.
>> AND THEY ARE GOING TO STAY
DOWN FOR A LITTLE BIT BECAUSE
PEOPLE ARE WORRIED ABOUT THE
MEDICARE THING
I THINK YOU HAVE TO -- GIVE IT
BIRTH.
BECAUSE WHEN OBAMA CAME IN,
THESE STOCKS MULTIPLES GOT
CRUSHED.
I WANT TO WAIT A FEW MORE DAYS
UNTIL PEOPLE REALIZE THAT IT IS
NOT THE END OF THE WORLD FOR
HEALTH CARE.
I NEED TO GO TO MICHAEL IN
NEBRASKA
MICHAEL.
>> Caller: HEY, JIM.
I WAS WONDERING HOW AMD IS
LOOKING.
>> I LIKE AMD AND THEY HAVE A
NEW GAME
THEY HAVE NEW TWITCH
AMD AND -- I'M TRYING TO
REMEMBER -- TWITCH, DON'T QUOTE
ME ON THAT
MY FRIENDS AT FEMA WILL GIVE ME
SOMETHING POSITIVE
I LIKE NVIDIA AND AMD.
AND JOHNNY IN CALIFORNIA
JOHN
>> Caller: BOO-YAH, JIM.
WE LOVE YOU OUT HERE IN
SACRAMENTO.
>> I'M THINKING ABOUT LIVING OUT
THERE, THE OLD DAYS WHEN I SAW
SMART AND FINAL GOT A BID.
WHAT IS GOING ON.
>> Caller: I FINALLY -- ME AND
THE CAVE MEN GOT RID OF GILEAD I
GOT IT AT 96 AND SOLD IT AT 63
AND IT NEVER TRICKLED DOWN TO
ME
WHAT IS THAT.
>> THEY HAVE A LOT OF CASH BUT
HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING WITH IT.
THEY HAVE A -- THEY HAVE TO
RATTLE THE CAGE IN THAT JOINTS
AND THAT, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
THAT IS "THE LIGHTNING ROUND."
>> Announcer: "THE LIGHTNING
ROUND" IS SPONSORED BY TD
AMERITRADE
the hesitation?
Eh, it just feels too
complicated, you know?
Well sure, at first, but JJ can
help you with that.
JJ, will you break it down for
this gentleman?
Hey, Ian. You know, at TD
Ameritrade, we can walk you
through your options
trades step by step
until you're comfortable.
I could be up for that.
That's taking options trading
from Wall St. to Main St.
Hey guys, wanna play some pool?
Eh, I'm not really a pool guy.
What's the hesitation?
It's just complicated.
Step-by-step options trading
support from TD Ameritrade
Internet that puts
you in charge.
Alright boys, time to eat.
That handles anything.
[ crowd cheering ]
That protects
what's important.
And reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
>>> I'M NOT GOING TO LIE, IT
FEELS GOOD TO BE RIGHT
LAST FRIDAY PACK OIM HAD A
TAKEOVER BID FROM CHEVRON.
VERSUS WHERE THE STOCK WENT OUT
THE DAY BEFORE
I CALLED IT.
I PREDICTED THIS DEAL WOULD
HAPPEN AND I'M BETTING IT IS THE
FIRST OF MANY MAJOR ACQUISITIONS
IN THE OIL AND GAS SPACE
WHEN I SAY I CALLED IT, I'M NOT
TALKING ABOUT THE FACT THAT
WE'VE OWNED IT BUT FOLLOW ALONG
BY JOIN THE CLUB
HONESTLY, THAT IS NOTHING TO
BRAG ABOUT
AND IT HAS BEEN AN AGONIZING
POSITION BECAUSE BEFORE CHEVRON
CAME ALONG THE STOCK SPENT
MONTHS AND MONTHS --
>> THE HOUSE OF PAIN.
>> IT IS GOOD TO BUST OUT OF MY
PERSONAL SHAWSHANK
BUT STILL THREE WEEKS AGO I DID
MAKE A SHOT AND EXPLAINED THIS
MARKET WAS IN NEED OF
ACQUISITIONS AND WE HAVE TOO
MANY PUBLICLY TRADED COMPANIES
AND WILL GET WORSE AS MORE AND
MORE PRIVATELY HELD UNICORNS
LIKE PINTEREST BECOME PUBLIC
AND THAT IS THE POINT I WAS
MAKING WHEN I TALKED ABOUT
POTENTIAL TAKEOVER TARGETS
TAKE A LOOK.
>> THERE ARE JUST TOO MANY OIL
COMPANIES.
I THINK THE MID-SIZE NEED TO
BAND TOGETHER TO CUT COSTS
APACHE AND ANNA DARKA MAKE MOST
SENSE.
THAT CRAMER GUY HAS GOOD IDEAS
WHY DID I THINK IT WAS A NATURAL
TAKEOVER TARGET?
I'LL LET HIM EXPLAIN.
>> ANADARKO WOULD BE GOOD FIT
FOR THE MAJORS
IT HAS HOLDINGS ALL OVER THE
WORLD BUT DINGED BY HIGHER
PRODUCTION COSTS WHICH PREDICTED
TO THE 40% EARNINGS MISS THAT
GUTTED THE STOCK IN FEBRUARY
SO IT WAS AN ATTRACTIVE TAKEOVER
PRODUCT.
WHEN THE NEWS BROKE, ONE ANALYST
JOKED THAT, AFTER 30 YEARS OF
TAKEOVER SPECULATION, IT IS
GETTING ACQUIRED
ALWAYS A BRIDESMAID AND NEVER A
BRIDE UNTIL NOW.
THIS IS A BIGGER GAME-CHANGER
THAN ANYONE IS SAYING.
IT REALLY IS
AND FOR CHEVRON, THE LARGEST
PRODUCER IN THE BASIN AN AREA OF
TEXAS OVERFLOWING WITH OIL THAT
IS SUPER CHEAP TO GET OUT OF THE
GROUND, IT IS A BIG DEAL
BUT WE HAVE TO ASK, WHO IS NEXT?
BECAUSE WE ALREADY KNOW, BUT
WHAT IS THE NEXT COMPANY
AND I'M EXTREMELY CONFIDENT
WE'LL SEE MORE CONSOLIDATION IN
THE OIL INDUSTRY
THE SAME THAT MADE IT A SWEET
BUY FOR CHEVRON MEANS THAT THE
RIVALS WOULD BE TERRIFIC
TAKEOVER FOR THE OIL COMPANIES
THAT WANT TO SIMMER DOWN BEFORE
I COME OUT WITH THE PIECE BUT
I'M PREDICTING COMPANIES WILL
GOBBLE UP BY THE INTEGRATED OR
LARGER EMP
WHY IS THAT?
FOR STARTERS, WE HAVE WAY TOO
MANY OIL PRODUCER AND ONE DEAL
DOES NOT CHANGE THAT
OVER THE PAST THREE YEARS THE
PRICE OF CRUDE HAS BEEN STUCK
BETWEEN THE MID-40s AND MID-70s.
EVERY TIME WE APPROACH THE HIGH
END COMPANIES PRODUCE THE OIL
PRODUCTION AND PRICES COME BACK
DOWN
BUT ONE A COMPANY GETS MERGED
OUT, THE REMAINING PLAYERS ADD
NEW CAPACITY
MORE IMPORTANTLY, THESE OIL
PRODUCERS, ESPECIALLY THE ONES
IN THE PERMIAN BASIN ARE
COMPETING FOR RESOURCES AND A
LIMITED SUPPLY OF PIPELINE AND
LABOR.
CONSOLIDATION COULD CONTAIN THE
COSTS.
AND THE MORE OBVIOUS, MULTIPLE
BIDDERS FOR ANADARKO
THANKS TO FANTASTIC REPORTING
FROM MY "SQUAWK ON THE STREET"
TEAM, WE KNOW THAT OXY PETROLEUM
TRIED TO BUY THEM AND THE OFFER
WAS HIGHER THAN CHEVRON'S $65
SHARE BID.
AND THEY SAID THEY WERE WILLING
TO PAY IN THE MID-70s PER SHARE,
INCLUDING ENORMOUS AMOUNTS OF
STOCK AND IT SEEMS LIKE ANNA
DARKA WOULD HAVE THEM BETTER
THAN CHEVRON
BUT WE DO KNOW THAT OX DENTAL
WANTS TO MAKE A DEAL AND CAME
WITHIN INCHES OF GETTING
ANADARKO
THEY HAVE THE FIRE POWER LINED
UP AND I BET THEY ARE NOT THE
ONLY ONE WITH THE FIRE POWER
ONCE THE ACQUISITION CLOSES,
CHEVRON WILL BECOME NEARLY AS
LARGE AS EXXON-MOBIL AND SHELL
IN TERMS OF PRODUCTION
I DON'T THINK EXXON WANTS TO SEE
THE CROWD WITHOUT A FIGHT.
THEY HAVE -- WELL OXY HAS
CLAIMED THEY HAVE THE PERMIAN
CROWN AND ALL OF THE COMPANIES
ARE FAR AND AWAY THE LARGEST OIL
AND GAS FORMATION EVER IN THE
U.S.
AND SO MUCH OF THAT STUFF IS SO
EASY TO GET OUT OF THE GROUND.
IT HAS PIPES AND EVERYTHING.
AND IF THEY COULD BULK UP THE
BUSINESS BY BUYING AN
INDEPENDENT THAT WOULD MAKE A
TON OF SENSE
SO WHICH INDEPENDENT PRODUCERS
WOULD MAKE THE MOST OBVIOUS
TARGETS.
I'LL GIVE THEM TO YOU.
WRITE THEM DOWN.
LAST ONE IS PROBABLY BEST BUT
ALL OF THESE WILL PROBABLY
HAPPEN
THE FIRST IS APACHE.
THEN CONCHO AND PARSLEY AND
PIONEER.
AND LET'S START WITH APACHE.
USED TO BE MUCH HIGHER AND EGYPT
AND A GOOD PLACE AND IN THE
NORTH SEA OFF THE COAST OF THE
BRITAIN.
MOST IMPORTANTLY, THEY HAVE A
TON OF EXPOSURE TO THE PERMIAN
BASIN BUT THE COMPANY HAS BEEN
INCONSISTENT PRODUCER.
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO WE LEARNED
OF A MAJOR NEW DISCOVERY, ALPINE
HIGH BUT NOT LIVED UP TO THE
EXPECTATIONS
THE HYPE WAS TERRIBLE.
AND PROBABLY BECAUSE THE
PROPERTY TURNED OUT TO BE LESS
OILY AND MORE GASSY AND OIL IS
MORE VALUABLE THAN GAS
THERE IS NO MARKET FOR THE DARK
STUFF.
BUT STILL APACHE STOCK HAS COME
DOWN TO RIDICULOUSLY LOW LEVELS.
THIS IS $101 STOCK FIVE YEARS
AGO AND IT BOTTOMED AT $25 AT
CHRISTMAS.
I THINK IT HAS MORE UPSIDE
YOU HAVE TO LIKE NATURAL GAS
AND THEY DO HAVE A DEBT-LADEN
BALANCE SHEET AND I THINK THIS
IS THE PRODUCER THAT MIGHT BE
WORTH MORE TO EXXON ON ON ITS
OWN.
AND NEXT UP CONCHO
IT IS TRANSFORMED INTO A NICE
EASY TO UNDERSTAND WELL-RUN AND
PURE PLAY IN THE PERMIAN BASIN
IF I'M RUNNING OXY DENTAL I
WOULD BE SALIVATED BUT THEY'VE
BEEN WORKING HARD TO CREATE A
STRAIGHTFORWARD BEST OF BREED
COMPANY AND WITH THE CLEANER
STRUCTURE, CONCHO IS IN A
TERRIFIC POSITION TO COIN MONEY
AND FOR THE RIGHT PRICE MAYBE
THEY AGREE TO BE ACQUIRED AND
OVERALL 6.6% AND [ INAUDIBLE ]
AND THEY HAVE GOOD HOLDINGS
ACROSS TWO OF THE BEST SUB AREAS
OF THE PERMIAN AND I THINK THEY
ARE POISED TO TRANSITION FROM
HEAVY INVESTMENT TO TREMENDOUS
PROFITS AND PLUS A BITE SIZE
TAKEOVER TARGET AND STOCK IS
CHEAP AT 5 FINALSE EARNINGS AND
THE BEST ONE IS LAST, PIONEER
NATURAL.
IT WOULD BE A MAJOR DEAL IF IT
WAS BOUGHT
PERHAPS EVEN MORE SIGNIFICANT
THAN ANADARKO.
DEPENDING ON THE SIZE OF THE
PREMIUM.
THIS IS RIGHT IN THE CROSS-HAIRS
AND IT DEFINITELY, I THINK, THE
BEST OF THESE FOUR COMPANIES
NOW PIONEER'S FOUNDING CEO SCOTT
SHEFFIELD STEPPED DOWN IN 2016
HANDING THE REIN TO JIM DUB BE
ANNOUNCED THE RETIREMENT AFTER A
HIDEOUS QUARTER.
IT WAS ABRUPT AND SHOCKING
WHO IS E.R.A. PLACING HIM?
65-YEAR-OLD SHEFFIELD.
I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED IF HE
WANTS TO PUT THE WHOLE BUSINESS
UP FOR SALE.
AND I'M NOT ALONE THERE.
AND THERE IS A REASON IT JUMP
11%.
I LOVE THIS COMPANY.
SHEFFIELD MADE BRILLIANT
ACQUISITIONS AND SUCH A SMART
GUY.
THINK A TACIT NEGOTIATOR, HE'LL
GET THE HIGHEST PRICE IF HE DOES
SELL
BOTTOM LINE, ANNA DARKA WON'T BE
THE LASTOND SO I LIKE APACHE AND
CONCHO AND PARSLEY AND PIE --
PIE ON EAR AND EVEN IF THEY
DON'T NEED CONSOLIDATION I THINK
PIONEER SHEFFIELD WILL FIND A
WAY TO MAKE MONEY FOR YOU.
STICK WITH CRAMER.
Through the AT&T Network,
Edge-to-Edge Intelligence gives
you the power to see every
corner of your growing business.
From using feedback to
innovate...
To introducing products
faster...
To managing website inventory...
and network bandwidth.
Giving you a nice big edge over
your competition.
That's the power of Edge-to-Edge
Intelligence.
>>> PEOPLE ASK ME WHAT IS YOUR
FAVORITE CANNABIS STOCK.
IT IS CANOPY
THEY HAVE THE MONEY AND THEY'VE
GOT THE SKILL.
I LIKE TO SAY THERE IS ALWAYS A
BULL MARKET SOMEWHERE AND I'LL
FIND IT FOR YOU HERE ON "MAD
MONEY.
I'M JIM CRAMER AND I'LL SEE YOU
TOMORROW