>> FIRST OF ALL, THERE ARE
PEOPLE THAT ARE WATCHING THAT
ARE GETTING MARRIED IN THE FALL
AND A LOT OF THEM WILL THINK TO
PLAY THAT SONG
>> NOBODY WOULD THINK TO PLAY
THIS SONG.
>> THIS SIS SO OLD, AND WE ARE
FAMILY, THE SISTER SLEDGE SONG
I ENCOURAGE YOU FOLKS, IF YOU'RE
THINKING ABOUT IT, DON'T DO IT
>> THE MORE YOU KNOW
>> WELCOME, DAN.
>> WHAT WAS THE QUESTION
>> NO, I KNOW WHAT THE QUESTION
IS
CAN THE TECH HEAVY WEIGHTS GO
UP
FACEBOOK SCARES ME, BUT THERE
ARE NAMES THAT MAKE SOME SENSE
AND WE HEADED SIMILARLY TO THE
SHOW ABOUT A MONTH AND A HALF
TWO MONTHS AGO AND I SAID THERE
WAS ANOTHER RADAR STOCK IN TECH
THAT PEOPLE HAVEN'T LOOKED AT
THAT WAS $230 RIGHT BEFORE
PRESIDENT TRUMP STARTED THESE
TEARIVES AND IT TRADED DOWN 130
AND IT TRADED TO THE UPSIDE AND
IT WAS LAM RESEARCH AND THEY
REPORTED AND 5G IS ALL THE RAGE
AND AT 13 TIMES FORWARD EARNINGS
IT'S A REASONABLE VALUATION.
SO IF YOU'RE LOOK FOR EXAMPLE A
PLACE THAT NOT A LOT OF PEOPLE
TALK ABOUT IT'S LRCX
>> IS IT TROUBLING THAT SOME OF
THESE LARGEST CAP COMPANIES IN
THE NASDAQ 100 AREN'T QUITE
THERE YET?
I DON'T KNOW THAT THAT'S
TROUBLING IN A SENSE
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS THE LAST
TIME I WAS ON THE SHOW
TECH IS THE MOST CYCLICAL SECTOR
THAT'S OUT THERE AND ON A LOT OF
DIFFERENT METRICS AND THE FACT
THAT SOME OF THESE STOCKS
HAVEN'T DONE WELL, SOME OF THESE
STOCKS ARE CYCLICAL AND YOU LOOK
AT THIS QUARTER'S EARNINGS AND
THE TECH EARNINGS WILL BE DOWN
10% AND THAT'S WHAT'S BAKED INTO
CONSENSUS RIGHT NOW.
PEOPLE FORGET THAT THESE ARE
CYCLICAL STOCKS AND THE PROFIT
CYCLE IS SLOWING RIGHT NOW
SO I THINK PEOPLE NEED TO
RECOGNIZE THAT AND A LOT OF
THESE STOCKS THAT YOU MENTION
ARE THE ONES THAT YOU'RE SEEING
THE HIT AND APPLE IS A GREAT
EXAM EXAMPLE OF THAT
>> THE FACT THAT THE
SEMICONDUCTOR INDEX DID TO ME
WHAT'S A BLOW-UP TOP AND IF YOU
GET SLOW ARE EARNINGS AND A
VERTICAL TOP MARKET AND THEY'VE
BEEN THE LEADERS AND REMEMBER,
THEY TOPPED OUT AND STARTED
GOING LORE BEFORE THE OCTOBER
AND NOVEMBER SOON.
>> WE PLAYED CELEBRATION AT THE
TOP OF THE SHOW WHICH IS
SUPPOSED TO BE SOMETHING VERY
GOOD
>> NO, NO.
I DON'T THINK IT'S THAT GOOD
I THINK CASH WILL STAY DOWN ON
APPLE, NOT THAT, TO ME
SEMICONDUCTOR NAME WILL BE MUCH
MORE CYCLICAL THAN A FANG-TYPE
NAME AND THE EUPHORIA THERE, I
DON'T KNOW THAT THE FAJS ARE TOO
CHEAP.
THE ONES I DO OWN I THINK ARE
CHEAP AND THAT'S ALWAYS THE WAY
IT IS.
ALPHABET, FACEBOOK, THOSE
REPRESENT REAL VALUE AND SO I'M
LONG THOSE AND I HOPE THAT THEY
GO UP AND THE SEMIS DON'T
COLLAPSE -- NOT COLLAPSE, BUT
DON'T COME IN A LOT AND THAT'S
WHY I THINK THE VALUE IS
I WOULDN'T BE CHASING SEMIS
HERE.
>> TO SORT OF KEY OFF WHAT THESE
GUYS ARE SAYING DO YOU THEN WANT
TO MOVE INTO THE MORE VALUE AREA
OF THE CYCLICAL SECTORS AT THIS
POINT?
>> FOR EXAMPLE, THE BANKS.
>> THE BANKS.
>> FOR EXAMPLE --
>> THE MOST VALUABLE IN THE MOST
CYCLICAL SECTOR, RIGHT
AND OBVIOUSLY THE BANKS HAVE HAD
A NICE RUN AND I'M SURPRISED BY
HOW WELL THEY TRADED AND I
LOOKED AT THAT TIME AND MAYBE IT
MAKES SENSE AND YOU LOOK AT
GOLDMAN SACHS HOVERING AROUND
208 AND THAT'S THE BOOK VALUE OF
THE STOCK WHEN THEY REPORTED A
COUPLE OF DAYS AGO
BANKS THAT ARE TRADING BOOK
VALUE.
YEAH, YOU CAN SEE HOW THAT MAKES
SENSE AND J.P. MORGAN WHICH IS
TRADING TWO TIMES PRICE TO
TANGIBLE BOOK WHICH IS A
DIFFERENT CONVERSATION AND YOU
HAVE TO WONDER ARE THEY AHEAD OF
THEMSELVES AND TO PUSH BACK ON
TECH A LITTLE BIT.
FACEBOOK HAS BEEN IMPERVIOUS TO
EVERY BIT OF BAD NEWS THAT'S
COME ACROSS THE HELM AND THERE'S
BEEN A LOT OF IT OVER THE LAST
COUPLE OF MONTHS
YOU HAVE TO WONDER AT A CERTAIN
POINT GIVEN THE RUN IS THE BAD
NEWS GOING COVER UP AND THE ONLY
THING THAT SAVED IT, AND IF THAT
WERE EVER TO CHANGE, LOOK OUT
BELOW ON FACEBOOK.
MY OPINION
>> THE PROCTER & GAMBLE CEO SAID
HE WAS RE-EXAMINING THE AD SPEND
BECAUSE OF THE NEGATIVE PRESS
AROUND IT.
WE'RE NOT TOO LONG AWAY FROM
FACEBOOK'S EARNINGS.
>> WE'RE NOT
TO ME, FACEBOOK HAS
IDIOSYNCRATIC ISSUES AND IT IS
UNCLEAR IF THAT'S GOING TO WORK.
NOT ONLY THAT, THEY'RE TRYING TO
HAVE THIS PRIVACY FIRST AND
AGAIN, WHEN YOU'RE TIEING TO DO
THAT, AND I DON'T WANT TO CALL
IT A TURNAROUND STORY, BUT IT
REMINDS ME VERY MUCH OF A
TURNAROUND STORY AND I DON'T
THINK IT WILL TRADE AS MUCH WITH
THE MARKET AND IT MAY BE A GOOD
VALUE, BUT IF I LOOK AT THE
FANGS IN THEM AND TO ME APPLE IS
THE ONE THAT LOOKS THE BEST IF
YOU'RE LOOKING TO BUY SOMETHING
AND I THINK THAT'S MORE
DEFENSIVE THAN ANYTHING ELSE
BECAUSE OF THEIR RELATIVELY
STEADY EARNINGS STREAK
>> SO, DAN, IS THIS ALL A CUE
FOR INVESTORS TO SAY I WANT TO
BE IN THE CYCLICAL AREAS OF THE
MARKET, BUT I WANT TO BE IN
THOSE THAT ARE MORE VALUE
ORIENTED AT THIS POINT
>> I WOULD DISAGREE WITH THE
WHOLE THESIS ALTOGETHER.
>> OKAY.
WHEN THE PROFIT CYCLE IS SLOWING
YOU DON'T WANT TO OWN CYCLICALS
BECAUSE THOSE ARE THE THINGS
THAT WILL HAVE THE WORST
EARNINGS TRENDS AND IT DOESN'T
MATTER IF THEY'RE VALUE
CYCLICALS AND HIGH GROWTH
CYCLICALS.
YOU WANT TO TONE DOWN YOUR
OPTIMISM ON THE WHOLE SPACE.
>> SO THE RECENT BID IN BANK
STOCKS, FOR INSTANCE
BAD NEWS THERE
>> I THINK WHAT'S HAPPENING THIS
YEAR AND WE TALKED ABOUT THIS
LAST TIME IS THAT EVERYBODY IS
GETTING CALLED OUT ON THIS
WHAT'S BEEN GOING THIS YEAR
TRADE, RIGHT
TECH IS ONE OF THE BEST
PERFORMING SECTORS AND ALL OF
THE CYCLICALS ARE DOING WELL AND
IT'S A REVERSAL OF WHAT HAPPENED
LAST YEAR.
SO PEOPLE ARE ASSUMING THAT
WHAT'S HAPPENING IN THIS YEAR IS
THIS, TODAY'S FUNDAMENTALS AND
IT'S ABOUT FOURTH QUARTER
FUNDAMENTALS AND REVERSING THAT.
IF YOU TAKE THAT OUT OF IT THE
CYCLICALS HAVEN'T DONE THAT
WELL
THE CYCLICALS HAVE DONE THAT
BELL AND THE DEFENSIVE STUFF,
AND IT WILL BE THE STUFF THAT
MATTERS MORE.
>> I THINK THE BANKS ARE A PROXY
FOR THE U.S. ECONOMY, ECONOMY,
LET'S JUST SAY, THEY'VEL SHOWN
THEY CAN BE PROFITABLE AND BE
THEY DON'T EVERYBODY IT P-E, AND
THAT'S A POSITIVE TO ME.
LOOKING AT SOMETHING LIKE AN
INDUSTRIAL OR SICK NICKAL LIKE A
URI WHICH I EARN
BIG EARNINGS OUT TONIGHT AND
THEY'RE JUST REAFFIRMING AND THE
STOCK'S UP A LOT AND PEOPLE ARE
NERVOUS THAT THE CALL WAS
SLOWING AND IT LOOKS LIKE WHAT
THEY'RE TELLING YOU IS THEY'RE
NOT SEEING THAT.
THEY'RE SEEING STRENGTH OUT
THERE AND SO I THINK THAT AS
LONG AS WE CONTINUE TO SEE GOOD,
ECONOMIC DATA OR GOOD EARNINGS,
I THINK THE MARKET DOES HAVE
MORE TO RUN.
HOWEVER, I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS
WITH THE VIX IN HERE
I HAVE TO BUY MORE PUTS.
>> SO THE POINT IS WE HAVE GOOD
ECONOMIC NEWS.
THAT'S WHAT CONCERNED ME TODAY
IS WE HAD GOOD ECONOMIC NEWS
FROM CHINA
IF YOU HAD TOLD ME THAT WE'D
HAVE A TRADE DEAL SIGNED BY THE
END OF MAY I WOULD HAVE TOLD YOU
THE DOW WAS UP 300 POINTS AND A
THESE LEVELS IT DOESN'T SEEM
LIKE THE DRIVERS WHO HAVE DRIVEN
THIS UP AND LOW INTEREST RATES
BY THE FED AND THE POTENTIAL FOR
A TRADE DEAL AND IMPROVING
ECONOMY, ALL OF THOSE HAVE BEEN
PRICED IN.
WE NEED THIS NEW PIECE OF
INFORMATION THAT WILL MOVE THE
MARKET AND MY CONCERN IS WITH
THIS RALLY THAT NEW PIECE OF
INFORMATION MOVES THE MARKET
LOWER AND LOOK AT HOW THE VIX
TRADED TODAY
IT CLOSED NEAR THE HIGHS OF THE
DAY.
>> I MEAN, THE QUESTION IS WITH
ALL THIS SAID COULD A CHINA
TRADE DEAL BE A SELL THE NEWS,
VENT WITH WHERE WE ARE IN THE
CYCLE AND WITH VALUATION AND THE
LACK OF REACTION IN THE MARKS
AND IT COULD JUST BE THAT ALL OF
THESE THINK'S HEAD LINES THAT
HAS COME OUT
EVERY DAY THERE IS A DIM
INUSHING TRADE LINE, AND STEVE
MNUCHIN SAYS PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
BEATED ABOUT IT AND HE HADN'T
MOVED IT AT ALL, AND WE'RE 75%
FROM THE S&P AND THE MARKET
CONTINUES TO LEVITATE HERE IN MY
OPINION BECAUSE THE CENTRAL BANK
AND THE FEDERAL RESERVE DID A
TOTALLY ABOUT FACE TWO OR THREE
MONTHS AGO AND THAT TO ME IS THE
BIG DRIVER AND THE HOPE OF A
CHINA TRADE DEAL
I'LL SAY THIS, THE CHINESE MARK
HAS COME RAKING BACK.
>> AND THE DATA HAS COME RAGING
BACK
AGAIN, MY OPINION AND WHY WOULD
THE CHINESE BE IN SUCH A SUHURR
WITH THE UNITED STATES RIGHT
NOW?
>> IF THEY DON'T THE MARKET
WOULD GO DOWN A LOT.
THIS IS A LONGER TERM THING,
RIGHT?
THEY CAN'T TIME THE MARKET WHEN
YOU DO IT.
>> SINCE THERE ARE BANKS LENDING
THE EQUIVALENT OF THE GDP OF
SWITZERLAND, YEAR TO DATE AND
THINGS LIKE THAT HELP.
>> ALSO WE HAVE ANOTHER FIGHT ON
OUR HANDS WITH EUROPE,
POTENTIALLY AND I DON'T THINK IT
WILL STOP THERE.
YOU HAVE A PRESIDENT THAT FIGHTS
WITH DEAD GUYS AND THEY'LL
CERTAINLY FIGHT WITH ANYBODY
ELSE IN THE WORLD AND THAT'S A
BIG RISK TO THE MARKET
>> I THINK THE ONE THING THAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, SHOULD YOU
BUY THE S&P HERE
SHOULD YOU BUY CYCLICALS
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO BUY CHOIN
A RIGHT?
IF THE DATA IS IMPROVING IN
CHINA THE DATA IS GETTING WORSE,
THE SIMPLE ANSWER IS DON'T TALK
ABOUT BUYING U.S. CYCLICALS AND
I THINK THERE'S MORE ROOM TO
RUN.
>> OR ONE SEPARATE MOVE.
WOULD YOU BUY EUROPE
>> NO.
SO YOU CAN BUY THE SECOND
DERIVATIVE PLAY AND WHY BUY THE
SECOND DERIVATIVE PLAY WHEN
THERE'S PLENTY OF UPSIDE THERE
>> EUROPE'S RUN A BIT TOO,
RIGHT?
TO ME CHINA HAS THE MORE UPSIDE
AND YOU WANT TO SEE COPPER HAD A
GREAT BREAKOUT AND THAT TENDS TO
BE A CHINA PROXY IN A SENSE AND
YOU CAN LOOK AT FREEPORT MAC AND
THAT MAY BE ONE WAY TO PLAY IT
AND TO DAN'S POINT, WHY NOT BUY
THE SHANGHAI AND IT'S GOT A TON
OF ROOM TO RUN.
>> THE HEALTH CARE SECTOR HAS
BEEN FEELING SOME HURT LATELY
AND IT'S OUR CHART OF THE DAY
AND THE WORST PERFORMING SECTOR
IN THE S&P 500
THE CAUSE, THE HEALTH INSURERS
LIKE UNH, CIGNA, ANTHEM AND
HUMANA WEIGHING ON THE SECTOR
AND ONE OF THE TRADERS THINKS
HEALTH CARE MIGHT BE THE CURE
AND YOU ALLUDED TO THIS
DEFENSIVE.
>> WHEN THE PROFIT CYCLE IS
SLOWING YOU HAVE TO BUY MORE
DEFENSIVE SECTORS AND YOU TALK
ABOUT TECH AND FINANCIALS AND
TECH AND FINANCIALS ARE TWO OF
THE THREE WORST PERFORMING
SECTORS AS THE PROFIT CYCLE IS
SLOWING AND WE LOOK AT PROFITS,
LIQUIDITY AND SENTIMENT AND
PROFITS AND TOP BUYING GROWTH
FOR THE HEALTH SQUARE SECTOR IS
ONE OF THE BEST IN THE S&P AND
THEY'RE THE ONLY SECTOR WHERE
ANALYSTS ARE TAKING UP TOP LINE
AND BOTTOM LINE ESTIMATES AND
THEY'RE CHEAP ON BASICALLY EVERY
METRIC YOU HAVE.
SO I THINK THERE IS A HUGE
DEMOGRAPHIC STORY IN THERE AND
TO GET THAT DEMOGRAPHIC STORY
OUT OF HISTORY IS A GREAT
OPPORTUNITY BECAUSE IT'S TRADING
OFF OF THE HEADLINE.
THIS IS NOT NEW NEWS AND THIS IS
PROBABLY GOING TO BE PART OF THE
SECTOR STORY FOR A LONG TIME AND
IT'S GOING TO BE A VERY
POLITICAL HOT-BUTTON ISSUE AND
ESPECIALLY AS WE GET CLOSER TO
THE ELECTION, BUT THIS IS NOT
DISSIMILAR TO THE FACT THAT A
COUPLE OF YEARS AGO HILLARY
TWEETED ABOUT DRUG PRICING AND
SHE WILL CRACK DOWN ON THE
WEIGHT IN THE NEAR-TERM AND OVER
THE LONG TERM, IF PROFIT CYCLES
ARE TURNING AND THAT WILL DO
WELL FOR THE SECTOR.
>> YOU BOUGHT ANTHEM JUST THE
OTHER DAY.
>> I HAD TO GOING INTO THIS AND
THEN I BOUGHT SOME TWO DAYS AGO,
AND I TRIED TO BUY SOME TODAY
AND I TRIED TO BUY SOME OPTIONS
TODAY AND THEY WERE THIN AND
WIDE, SO UNFORTUNATELY, I DIDN'T
GET ANYTHING DONE.
I THINK THAT THIS IS REALLY,
REALLY OVERDONE.
TWO DAYS AGO I BOUGHT IT AT A
MUCH WORSE PRICE THAN IT IS
TODAY, BUT EVERYTHING YOU'RE
SAYING THESE ARE GREAT COMPANIES
AND PROFITABLE COMPANIES AND
THEY ARE IN A SORT OF -- VORTEX
OF NEGATIVE NEWS AND SO I LIKE
IT WHEN THINGS TRADE DOWN BY
INTEGERS OR -- RIGHT
$10 AT A TIME NOW.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH LIKING IT AND I
WOULD PREFER TO BOTTOM OUT RIGHT
NOW, BUT I THINK IT'S VERY
ATTRACTIVE HERE.
I THINK YOU WILL SEE THIS DIE
DOWN AND WE'VE SEEN THIS THREAT
SEVERAL TIMES BEFORE OVER THE
LAST -- EVER SINCE OBAMA CARE,
AND I THINK YOU WOULD SEE IT
DRIVE DOWN AND THIS IS
TREMENDOUS VALUE
>> WHEN ARE THE ELECTIONS, GUY
NOT A TRICK QUESTION
IT'S WANT A TRICK QUESTION
>> NOVEMBER 2020, IS THAT RIGHT?
CAN THEY DO THAT DING DING
>> WHY DID I ASK YOU
>> BECAUSE YOU WANTED TO MAKE ME
LOOK FOOLISH
>> I KNEW BECAUSE THE HEADLINE
RISK TO THIS GROUP WILL LAST
THROUGH AT LEAST -- I AGREE WITH
THAT IN SOME WAYS AND I DISAGREE
WITH THAT.
>> I WANTED TO ADD ONE OTHER
POINT.
>> ANTHEM.
THEY HAVE $5 BILLION LEFT IN
THEIR BUY BACK
I DID CALL AND I DIDN'T HEAR
BACK AND MAYBE THEY'LL INCREASE
THEIR BUYBACK AND I DON'T THINK
THEY'LL BE OUT THERE BEFORE THEY
REPORT AND IT WOULD AREN'T BE
SURPRISING TO ME TO SEE SOME OF
THESE HMOs OUT THERE AND THEY DO
BIG BUYBACKS
>> BUT YOU ARE CORRECT
YOU HAVE UNTIL NOVEMBER 2020
WHEN THIS WILL BE IN THE
CROSSHAIRS TO A CERTAIN DEGREE
AND IT WILL WEIGH IN IN TERMS OF
THE RHETORIC
LOOK AT THE QUARTER YESTERDAY
WAS AN OUTSTANDING QUARTER AND
THEY ACTUALLY RAISED GUIDANCE.
YOU HAVE A STOCK THAT'S TRADING
AT 13 TIMES FORWARD EARNINGS AND
THE LAST FIVE-YEAR AVERAGE IS
TAKEN AND TRADING 21 TIMES
FORWARD EARNINGS AND THAT'S THE
GOOD NEWS.
THE BAD NEWS IS 96% OF THE
ANALYSTS HAVE A BUY ON IT AND I
DON'T THINK THERE ARE ANY SELLS
ON IT WHICH IS A BIT OF A
PROBLEM BECAUSE NOW YOU MIGHT
HAVE SOME ANALYST REVERSING
NUMBERS.
THAT BEING SAID, YOU ARE TALKING
ABOUT TROUGH VALUATIONS AT A
COMPANY THAT'S DOING
EXTRAORDINARILY WELL WHERE
PEOPLE ARE SHOOTING FIRST AND
ASKING QUESTIONS LATER
SO I THINK YOU HAVE TO BE
ONBOARD AND I DON'T THINK ANY OF
THIS STUFF WILL GO THROUGH AND
THE RHETORIC WILL DAY DOWN AND
UNH, WHENEVER IT IS NOW, 220 WAS
A GIFT.
>> AND LOOK AT THE E TRS F, XLV,
LOOK AT HOW IT TRADED TODAY.
HUGE VOLUME ON THIS PUKE TYPE OF
SDMING WHEN I FEEL LIKE I WANT
TO VOMIT ON MY SHOES THOSE ARE
THE BEST TRADES AND SO THAT'S
WHAT TODAY IN HEALTH CARE LOOK
LIKE
>> ALL RIGHT
WE HAVE BREAKING NEWS IN THE
CANNABIS SPACE FOR WEED WEEK,
IRONICALLY
IT'S BUYING ACREAGE HOLDINGS AND
THIS AFTER THE FLURRY OF DEALS
WE'VE SEEP IN THE SPACE.
ACCORDING TO SOURCES CLOSE TO
THE COMPANY THE TWO HAVE BEEN IN
TALKS FOR THE PAST TWO WEEKS AND
THEY'RE SKEDZ YOU WILLED TO HAVE
A CALL TONIGHT TO FINALIZE THE
DEAL AND POSSIBLY ANNOUNCE THIS
DEAL AS EARLY AS TOMORROW
MORNING AND THIS DEAL CAME
TOGETHER VERY QUICKLY.
CANOPY GROWTH WAS LOOKING AT
OTHER MULTI-STATE OPERATORS HERE
IN THE UNITED STATES AND IF YOU
THINK MORE BROADLY ABOUT THIS
DEAL AND WHAT THIS MEANS FOR THE
INDUSTRY, REMEMBER, THAT
CONSOLATION BRANDS IS A MAJOR
SHAREHOLDERS AND STAKE HOLDER IN
CANOPY GROWTH AND IT ALLOWS
CONSOLATION BRANDS TO HAVE A
PIECE OF THE U.S. CANNABIS
MARKET
SO IT IS BELIEVED BY INDUSTRY
INSIDERS THAT THIS COULD BE THE
TEMPLATE FOR A LOT MORE OF THESE
TYPES OF DEALS TO HAPPEN FOR
U.S. MAJOR COMPANIES TO HAVE A
PIECE OF THE U.S. CANNABIS
MARKET
SO THAT IS WHAT WE'RE WATCHING
TONIGHT.
WE'LL HAVE MORE DETAILS TO SEE
SOME OF THE OTHER TARGETS THAT
HAD BEEN APPROACHED BY CANOPY
LATER ON AND ALSO WE'VE GOT BEN
KOVLER, THE CEO OF GREEN THUMB,
AND WE'LL GET HIS TAKE ON WHAT
THIS COULD MEAN AND THIS COULD
BE A MAJOR DEAL AND CANOPY
GROWTH BUYING ACREAGE HOLDINGS.
>> NOT ONLY COULD THIS BE A BIG
DEAL, BUT THE TEMPLATE FOR OTHER
WAYS TO GET INTO THIS.
MANY COMPANIES HAVE BEEN TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT IS KIND OF
THE MOST -- THE BEST LEGAL WAY
TO GET INTO THIS WITHOUT RUNNING
ANY INTO ANY ISSUES.
THIS COULD BE THE WAY THAT THEY
DO IT.
IT COULD PUMP UP VALUATION, BUT
IT COULD BE GOOD FOR A TRADE
HERE IN THE ENTIRE FACE BECAUSE
THE WHOLE SPACE WILL A BE HIGHER
OR WHAT THE TAKEOVER VALUE IS.
>> OKAY.
MEANTIME, WE HAVE BREAKING NEWS.
ZOOM PRICING THE IPO
LET'S GET TO LESLIE PICKER FOR
THE PRICING.
>> MELISSA, THIS IS ACCORDING TO
A SOURCE WITH THE PRICING
DISCUSSIONS AND I AM TOLD THAT
ZOOM HAS PRICED ITS IPO AT $36
THAT IMPLIES AN OFFERING SIZE OF
$751 MILLION
A VALUATION OF $9.2 BILLION IN
THE OSMARKET CAP AND PRICING IT
DOLLAR ABOVE THE RANGE
I AM TOLD THAT THIS IFRP COULD
HAVE PRICED EVEN HIGHER THAN
THAT BASED ON THE DEMAND THAT
CAME IN THE DOOR AND THE COMPANY
WANTED TO STAY CONSERVATIVE TO
ENSURE A DEBUT TOMORROW.
>> LESLIE PICKER AT HEADQUARTERS
AND THIS WAS EXPECTED FOR THE
SOFTWARE COMPANY, PRICED ABOVE
THE RANGE?
ANYBODY FOLLOWING THIS
>> PRIVATELY, THEY HAD THIS
THING VALUED AT A BILLION.
WHAT DID LEASLIE VALUE IT?
9 BILLION.
>> PINTEREST, I HAVE A PAGE AND
WE TRADED TRADE IT OR FADE IT?
>> VALUE TRADE
AND I SAID VALUE TRADE.
>> KAREN MAKES A GOOD POINT.
IT'S NOT A VALUE AT ALL.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
UNVALUATION.
>> 60% REVENUE GROWTH.
I HAVE A BILLION USERS IN A
COUPLE OF YEARS AND THEY WENT
SLOW AND STEADY, PINTEREST
I KNOW BECAUSE I'VE HAD A PAGE
FOR AT LEAST THE LAST SIX OR
SEVEN.
>> I FEEL THAT MEANS THAT YOU
SHOULDN'T BUY IT
PINTEREST SHOULD REALLY CONTACT
YOU TO HAVE YOU TAKE YOUR PAGE
DOWN
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> OH, WOW
>> THE LAUGHTER IS FANTASTIC
>> THE ONE THING ABOUT THE ZOOM
PRICING, THOUGH, I THINK IT
PROBABLY ERASES THE NEGATIVE
TONE FROM THE LIFT PRICING AND
IT WENT ABOVE RANGE HERE AND
PEOPLE ARE CONCERNED THAT MAYBE
THE UNICORNS WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO
COME OUT ANDER
FORM AND WE'LL SEE HOW IT TRADE,
BUT THIS IS GENERALLY A POSITIVE
SIGN FOR THE IPO MARKET.
>> THE BIG DIFFERENCE IS IT
MAKES MONEY, RIGHT
APPARENTLY SOMETHING THAT'S NOW
ENVOGUE
EN VOGUE AND I THINK IT WILL BE
INTERESTING TO SEE HOW ZOOM
TRADES TOMORROW VERSUS
PINTEREST.
I MEAN -- I KNOW THAT'S A LOT OF
EBITDA AND A LOT OF GROWTH AND
STILL IT'S A LOT OF LOSSES, TOO.
>> COMING UP, ZOOM PRICING
MOMENTS AGO AND WE'RE STILL
AWAITING PINTEREST AND THE CEO
OF CASPAR IS HERE AS THE
MATTRESS DELIVERY GIANT IS
GEARING UP FOR ITS IPO
PLUS, LAS VEGAS SANDS JUMPING
AND WE'LL TELL YOU WHAT WALL
STREET IS SAYING ABOUT THE
QUARTER AND THERE IS A STOCK
GEARING UP FOR EARNINGS TOMORROW
AND TRADERS ARE BETTING IT IS
ABOUT TO CRASH
WERE A LIVE IN TIMES SQUARE IN
NEW YORK CITY.
MUCH MORE "FAST MONEY" AFTER
THIS
There's brushing...and
there's Oral-B Power brushing.
Oral-B just cleans better.
Even my hygienist said
going electric could lead to way
cleaner teeth.
And unlike Sonicare,
Oral-B is the first electric
toothbrush brand
accepted by the ADA.
Oral-B.
This is not a bed...
it's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed, from $999...
senses your movement and
automatically adjusts
on each side to keep
you both comfortable.
And snoring?
How smart is that?
Smarter sleep.
So you can come out swinging,
maintain your inner
focus, and wake up rested
and ready for anything.
Sleep Number is ranked #1
in Customer Satisfaction
with Mattresses by J. D. Power.
Save $400 on select Sleep
Number 360 smart beds.
Only for a limited time.
>>> KWELCOME BACK TO "FAST
MONEY," UPGRADING DOMINO'S PIZZA
WHILE DOWNGRADING CHIPOTLE AFTER
SHARES SOARED PAST THE 12-MONTH
PRICE TARGET AND CHECK OUT THE
GOLDEN ARCHES SERVING UP A FRSH
ALL-TIME HIGH AS THAT STOCK
CONTINUES TO GRIND HIGHER.
IF YOU WANT TO DIG INTO FAST
FOOD WHERE DO YOU GO AND
IRONICALLY I ASKED KAREN THIS
WHO DOESN'T EAT FAST FOOD.
>> BUT IF I DID I'D PROBABLY GO
TO McDONALD'S.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT EXPENSIVE
RELATIVE TO SOME OF THE OTHER
MAIMS AND THEY'VE BEEN EXECUTING
REALLY WELL.
CHIPOTLE, KUDOS TO THEM THEY'VE
DONE A FANTASTIC JOB, BUT I FEEL
LIKE THEY ARE ON THE HIGH WIRE
YOU IN
ANY TINY MISS AND THE
EXPECTATIONS ARE VERY HIGH COULD
REALLY EXECUTE CLOSER AND I
WOULD LIKE TO BE IN McDONALD'S
AND THE RISK REWARD IS MORE
ATTRACTIVE.
>> KUDOS TO PIPER JAFFRAY.
SHE'S BEEN THE AXE IN THE CMG
FOR THE LAST COUPLE HUNDRED
THERE ARES AND I THINK THE
VALUATION IS RIDICULOUS IN CMG
AND I'VE THOUGHT THAT FOR THE
LAST $150 AND EVEN McDONALD'S
NOW IS GETTING A LITTLE RICH
THEY'LL REPORT ON APRIL 30th AND
CLOSE TO 22 TIMES FORWARD
EARNINGS AND HISTORICALLY IT'S
THE LOFTIER, FROTHIER END FOR
THEM SO THEY BETTER CRUSH ON
APRIL 30th, BUT TO YOUR POINT
EARLIER IT CONTINUES TO BE SLOW
AND STEADY TO THE UPSIDE AND
MAYBE THE TRADE IN McDONALD'S
WILL PULL THE RIP CORD BEFORE
THEY REPORT.
>> McDONALD'S IS ROLLING OUT
THEIR TECH PLATFORM, RIGHT
IF YOU LOOK AT WHAT HAPPENED AND
THAT'S WHAT McDONALD'S IS DOING
JUST NOW AND IF THERE'S THE
OTHER COMPANIES ARE A GUIDE, ONE
MIGHT THINK THAT THEIR SALES AND
EARNINGS WILL INCREASE QUITE A
BIT BECAUSE OF THIS.
I WOULD STICK WITH THE
McDONALD'S.
>> WHEN THINGS ARE SLOWING IS A
DOLLAR MENU DEFENSIVE?
>> YEAH.
WE ARE PROBABLY WITHIN THE
DISCRETIONARY SPACE AND WITHIN
RESTAURANT, DEFINITELY
McDONALD'S WOULD OPERATE MORE
LIKE A STAPLES COMPANY
I WOULD JUST BE A LITTLE BIT,
AND I WOULD BE CAUTIOUS OVERALL
ON THOSE TYPES WAS NAMES BECAUSE
THEY'RE CYCLICAL, RIGHT?
I THINK THE ECONOMY IS DOING
WORSE AND YOU WANT TO AVOID
THOSE TYPES OF RESTAURANTS AND
TYPICALLY, THE BIG DEBATE RIGHT
NOW IS THE ECONOMY SLOWING AND
ARE PEOPLE GOING TO START LOSING
THEIR JOBS AND YOU SEE SOME
BOUNCING AROUND AND IF THAT
HAPPENS AND YOU WANT TO BE WAY
MORE CAUTIOUS ON THOSE TYPES OF
NAMES.
TO YOUR POINT ON TECHNOLOGY,
McDONALD'S ISN'T GOING TO BE THE
FIRST RESTAURANT TO ROLL OUT
TECHNOLOGY
THERE'S A LOT OF OTHER
RESTAURANTS WHO WILL REMAIN
NAMELESS, BUT THEY HAVE
TERRIBLE, TERRIBLE APPS THAT I
WON'T USE.
>> IT COULD BACKFIRE
>> I THINK STARBUCKS HAS A GOOD
ONE.
I THINK McDONALD'S --
>> SO YOU DON'T GO TO CHUCK E.
CHEESE
>> THEIR APP IS AMAZING.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> FOR MORE ON THE BIG ANALYST
CALLS OF THE DAY AND WHICH
STOCKS HAVE THE BIGGEST MOVES GO
TO CNBC.COM.
STILL AHEAD, THE IPO IS HAVING A
BOOM, AND WE AWAIT PINTEREST
WE WILL TALK TO THE CEO OF
CASPAR AS THE MATTRESS DELIVERY
GIANT COULD BE GEARING UP FOR
ITS IPO.
WE'LL ASK HIM.
MUCH MORE "FAST MONEY" COMING UP
RIGHT AFTER THIS
♪
>> WELCOME BACK TO DWOET FAST
MONEY.
IMF MADNESS IS IN FULL SWING
TWO TECH UNICORNING COMING UP
TONIGHT.
WE ARE STILL AWAITING PINTEREST.
LESLIE PICKER IS WITH US
>> ZOOM JUST PRICED ITS IPO AT
$36 A SHARE ACCORDING TO A
PERSON FAMILIAR WITH THE
DISCUSSIONS AND THAT VALUES THE
VIDEOCONFERENCING PROVIDER ABOVE
$9 BILLION
THE COMPANY HAD RAISED THE RANGE
IT INITIALLY MARKETED TO
INVESTORS ON STRONG DEMAND AND
THE $36 PER SHARE WAS ABOVE THAT
BOOSTED RANGE.
PINTEREST IS SET TO TIMIZE ITS
OWN IPO PRICE DURING A MEETING
THAT BEGINS IN ABOUT A HALF AN
HOUR OR SO
I AM TOLD THAT ONE WAS ALSO IN
DEMAND FROM INVESTORS AND AIMS
TO PRICE ABOVE THE RANGE IT HAD
BEEN MARKETING, AS WELL.
COMBINED, THOSE TWO COMPANIES
COULD UNLEASH MORE THAN THEIR 2
BILLION WORTH OF STOCK INTO THE
MARKETPLACE AND THEY COULD
REPRESENT A NICE RESET FOR THE
TECH IPO MARKET AS LYFT
CONTINUES TO TRADE ABOVE THE
PRICE, BUT THESE TWO AND EVERY
IPO COMES WITH EMBEDDED RISKS,
OF COURSE, ESPECIALLY FOR RETAIL
INVESTORS WHO TEND TO GET A MUCH
SMALLER PROPORTION OF THE
ALLOCAT
ALLOCATION EVEN THOUGH THEY SEEK
ALLOCATION IN PINTEREST.
THE TRADING TOMORROW SHOULD
PROVIDE A SENSE OF HOW INVESTORS
FEEL ABOUT PROFIT.
PINTEREST POSTED LOSSES ALTHOUGH
THEY WERE NARROWING WHILE ZOOM
WAS PROFITABLE AND BOTH
COMPANIES WERE SHOWING TOP LINE
GROWTH MORE THAN DOUBLING YEAR
OVER YEAR.
ZOOM WILL BE LISTED ON THE
NASDAQ UNDER THE SYMBOL ZM AND
PINTEREST WILL BE LISTED IN THE
NYSE UNDER PNS
>> BRIAN KELLY
>> THAT'S ME
>> WILL IT HELP A LITTLE BIT
>> I THINK IT DOES HELP A BIT.
I THINK IT WILL BE INTERESTING
HERE
THE FACT THAT ZOOM TRADED ABOVE
OR PRICED ABOVE IS VERY GOOD
WE'LL HAVE TO SEE HOW THEY BOTH
TRADE BECAUSE TO KAREN'S POINT
WE'LL GET WHAT THE MARKET FEELS
LIKE ABOUT WHETHER YOU WANT TO
HAVE REAL EARNINGS OR WHETHER
YOU WANT TO HAVE KIND OF GROWTH
IN THAT NETWORK EFFECT AND SO
FAR, LYFT HAS SAID MAYBE THAT'S
NOT THE BEST THING AND WE'LL SEE
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN PINTEREST
STARTS TRADING
THE NEXT TECH UNICORN COULD BE
AROUND THE CORNER.
KASPER IS A MATTRESS FIRM THAT'S
VALUED MORE THAN A BILLION
DOLLAR AND THE COMPANY HAS HIRED
UNDERWRITERS FOR ITS VERY OWN
IPO.
WHEN WILL UMP ABOARD THE IPO
MANIA.
WE ARE JOINED BY PHILIP KRIM
>> NO COMMENT ON CASPER IPO AND
GREAT FOR ZOOM AND PINTEREST AND
WE CERTAINLY THINK THE IPO
MARKET IS ROBUST AND GREAT TO
SEE SO MUCH EXCITEMENT.
>> THERE ARE A HANDFUL OF OTHER
ONLINE, DIRECT TO CONSUMER
MATTRESS COMPANIES
HOW DO YOU DIFFERENTIATE AMONGST
THEM
WHAT IF THEY DECIDE TO ALL GO
PUBLIC HERE?
WE THINK CASPER STAND ALONE AND
EVERYTHING WE DO IS ABOUT
HELPING OUR CUSTOMERS SLEEP
BETTER AND WE THINK ABOUT END TO
END ABOUT SLEEP AND IT'S ABOUT
THE GREAT MASS TRESS AND
EVERYTHING TO HELP YOU SLEEP AND
WE HELPED LAUNCH A LIGHTING
PRODUCT THAT HELPS YOU WAKE UP
BETTER AND SLEEP BETTER AND THE
MARKET END TO END ABOUT SLEEP
SOLUTIONS AND WE WANT TO BE THE
WORLD'S FIRST GLOBAL SLEEP BRAND
AND WE ARE WELL ON OUR WAY TO
DOING THAT
NOT THAT YOU LOOK AT COMPANIES
THAT ARE PUBLICLY TRADED, BUT IF
YOU DID, WHICH ONES ARE SIMILAR
TO YOU AND NOT NECESSARILY BEING
A MATTRESS COMPANY, BUT THE IDEA
OF WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO CREATE?
>> WE THINK WE'RE ONE OF THE
FIRST OF OUR KIND MEANING WE'RE
A DIGITALLY NATIVE, WITH
CASPER.COM
WE OPENED UP 23 RETAIL STORES.
WE HAVE GREAT PARTNERS WITH
FOLKS LIKE TARGET AND WE BELIEVE
THAT WE WILL HAVE A BUSINESS
WHERE NO MATTER HOW CONSUMERS
WANT TO SHOP FOR OUR PRODUCTS WE
HAVE GREAT PRODUCTS AND GREAT
EXPERIENCES AND WE THINK THERE
IS NOT A PUBLIC COMPANY COMP
THAT'S DONE THAT JOURNEY
>> GO AHEAD, B.K
>> YOU ANNOUNCED A NEW MATTRESS
THAT HAS THE BOX SPRINGS IN IT,
THE METAL.
WHEN YOU SHIP THOSE, DOES THAT
CHANGE THE MARGINS ON THE
MATTRESS VERSUS WHAT YOU WERE
DOING IN THE PAST?
>> YESTERDAY WE LAUNCHED THE
INNER SPRING TECHNOLOGY AND FOAM
TECHNOLOGY AND WE LAUNCHED TWO
DIFFERENT MODELS AROUND THAT
FOR US, WE ARE STILL ABLE TO
COMPRESS THOSE MATTRESSES, SHIP
THEM ANYWHERE IN THE COUNTRY AND
THEY'RE REALLY PHENOMENAL
PRODUCTS THAT WERE IN
DEVELOPMENT OVER A YEAR IN THE
CASPER LABS FROM SAN FRANCISCO
YOU CAN COMPRESS IT AND SHIP IT
ANYWHERE AND IT'S SUPER FUN TO
OPEN AND THEY SLEEP REALLY,
REALLY GREAT.
>> CAN WE TALK ABOUT THE UPSELL
THEN
AND IT'S A TECHNOLOGY COMPANY
AND SOMEBODY BUYS A MATTRESS AND
ARE THEY BUYING THE LIGHTING
PROCESS AND ARE THEY BUYING THE
PILLOWS AND THE SHEETS
>> THE PILLOWS
>> PEOPLE MIGHT HEAR PILLOW.
>> I HAVE TROUBLE SAYING LIKE
PILLOW IS WHAT I SAY
>> ANYWAY --
>> I FORGOT MY QUESTION.
HOPEFULLY YOU REMEMBER.
>> WE MAKE GREAT PILLOWS AND
GREAT SHEETS AND GREAT LIGHTING
PRODUCTS AND WE ARE SEEING
HIGHER AND HIGHER ATTACHMENT
RATES AND WE ARE SEEING REPEAT
REVENUE INCREASE DRAMATICALLY
AND WE'RE ONLY A 5-YEAR-OLD
COMPANY, ACTUALLY THIS MONTH AND
WE LAUNCHED APRIL 2014 AND AS WE
GET OUR CUSTOMERS TO BE MORE
MATURE WE'RE SEEING THEM COME
BACK TIME AND TIME AGAIN, TO BUY
MATTRESSES AND OUR FULL SUITE OF
PRODUCTS
>> I AM OLD FASHIONED IN BUYING
SOMETHING LIKE A MATTRESS.
I'LL BUY EVERYTHING ELSE ONLINE
INCLUDING FOOD AND SHAMPOO, BUT
NOT A MATTRESS
SO IF I ORDER IT AND I DON'T
WANT IT, THAT'S A PAIN IN THE
YOU KNOW WHAT TO RETURN, TO SEND
BACK
NO
>> WE CHANGED THE WAY THAT YOU
WOULD RETURN IT.
THE INDUSTRY, YES, IT'S A HUGE
PAIN, BUT WITH US, WE CALL US UP
AND WE'LL COME PICK UP THE
MATTRESS
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PACK IT BACK
UP AND WE DONATE IT LOCALLY AND
WE APPRECIATE THAT YOU GIVE US A
SHOT
WE CHANGED WAIT PEOPLE SHOP FOR
THE PRODUCTS AND WE HAVE 23
STORES THAT WE'VE OPENED
WE'RE OPENING UP OVER A DOZEN
THIS QUARTER
TWO THIS WEEK, IN FACT AND THOSE
STORES ARE A GREAT COMPLIMENT TO
THE ONLINE EXPERIENCE AND NO
MATTER HOW YOU WANT TO SHOP FOR
THE PRODUCTS WE WANT TO SOLVE
THAT.
>> GIVEN THOSE EMBEDDED COSTS?
>> NO PUN INTENDED, ARE YOU
MAKING MONEY ON EVERY MATTRESS
YOU SELL
>> WE DON'T BREAK OUT
PROFITABILITY, BUT CASPER HAS A
GREAT PRODUCT AND A GREAT
BUSINESS MODEL AND BY TAKING IT
TO MARKET BOTH ONLINE AND OFF
LINE THIS IT'S GROWING OUR
ONLINE BUSINESS IN A VERY
EFFICIENT WAY, SO WE THINK THIS
GO TO MARKET STRATEGY IS WORKING
WELL AND WE'RE IN THE EARLY DAYS
OF SCALING IT AND WE CAN KEEP
BUILDING IT OUT FOR YEARS TO
COME
>> PHIL, A THANKS FOR JOINING
US
PHILIP KRIM, THE CEO OF KRCASPE
>> YEAH, WHY NOT
IT'S BETTER THAN AN AIR
MATTRESS
OF COURSE, I WOULD DO THIS.
>> IT'S AN UPGRADE TO WHAT YOU
HAVE NOW.
>> YEAH.
YOU DON'T SLEEP ON AIR
MATTRESSES
>> OUR FUTONS.
>> SPEAKING OF UNICORN, WHY IN
THE WORLD, WHY IN THE WORLD IS
GUY ADAMI WEARING A UNICORN
ONESIE
A UNICORN ONESIE
WE'LL TELL YOU WHAT THAT'S ALL
ABOUT LATER IN THE SHOW AND
TRUST ME, YOU DO NOT WANT TO
MISS THAT.
>> THE POT STOCK SOARING AFTER
HOURS AND WE REPORTED THAT
CANOPY IS NEAR BING UYA DEAL
WITH ACREAGE HOLDINGS.
MUCH MORE "FAST MONEY" RIGHT
AFTER THIS
>> WELCOME BACK TO "FAST MONEY."
LAS VEGAS SANDS, SHARES OF THE
COMPANY GETTING A BOOST.
LET'S GO TO CONTESSA BREWER AT
HEADQUARTERS
>> HI, MELISSA
STRONG QUARTER FOR SAND ACROSS
THE BOARD.
THE COMPANY GETS MOST OF ITS
REVENUE STREAM FROM CHINA AND
THIS IS THE POSTER CHILD FOR THE
EMINFUELING PROFITS IN MACAU
IT'S WANT THE SO-CALLED WHALES
DRIVING THE PROFITS AND IT'S THE
PREMIUM MASS AND MASS GAMBLING
SEGMENTS
THE COMPS IN 2018 WERE STRONG
AND THE SMOKING BAN OBVIOUSLY
BEGAN THIS QUARTER AND MACRO
CONCERNS WERE OUT THERE AND VIP
IS SOFTENING AND YET AGAINST
THIS BACKDROP WE DELIVERED THE
BEST QUARTER SINCE 2014.
>> SET A RECORD IN MASS TABLE
THERE.
UP 13% OVER THE LAST YEAR AND
THE COMPANY IS INVESTING
$3.3 BILLION EXPANDING
MARINA-BASED SANDS IN SINGAPORE
AND THE COMPANY IS RUNG 98%
OCCUPANCY THERE AND THOUSANDS OF
NEW SUITES, HIGH-END
ENTERTAINMENT AND TOP RETAIL,
AND ATTRACTING AFFLUENT TOURISTS
WHO MAKE A PREMIUM MASS.
DAN KOWOZNIAK SAYS IT'S A VIP
MARKET
QUARTER TO QUARTER RESULTS CAN
BE LUMP PEP IN FACT, THE L BOX S
PRESIDENT CALLED IT VOLATILE
IT DOES NOT PRESENT THE BEST
GROWTH OPPORTUNITIES AND THE
COMPANY IS INVESTING HEAVILY IN
LAS VEGAS.
IT'S LAUNCHING THE SPEAR AND
THAT'S THE SPORT ARENA IN
PARTNERSHIP WITH MSG AND ONE
FINAL NOTE, MELISSA, AND SHELDON
ADELSON IS NOT ON THIS CALL AND
THE SECOND THAT HE'S MISSED AND
HE'S BEING TROEEATED FOR
NON-HODGKIN'S LYMPHOMA AND THE
TREATMENT MAKES HIM TIRED AND
HE'S STILL INVOLVED IN BOARD AND
COMPANY DECISIONS.
>> CONTESSA, THANK YOU
>> IF YOU LOOK AT THIS CHINA
DATA AND YOU THINK IT IS TURNING
TO THE UPSIDE.
>> IT'S DEFINITELY TURNING AND
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS
WYNN WAS UP 105 AND WE STARTED
TALKING ABOUT THIS, THE FACT
THAT THE CHINESE WERE THROWING
THE KITCHEN SINK AT THE ECONOMY
AND THEY WERE PROBABLY GOING TO
BE SUCCESSFUL IN GETTING THEIR
ASSET PRICES BACK UP AND THAT'S
COME TO FRUITION AND WYNN'S HAD
A DECENT MOVE AND LAS VEGAS SAND
HIS A MOVE AND LVS AT 19 TIMES
AND A LITTLE MORE EXPENSIVE THAN
WYNN
GOOD QUARTER AND THIS WAS AN $80
STOCK A FEW MOCKSNTHS AGO, AND
MIGHT OFFSET ANY PROBLEMS YOU
MIETS HAVE IN CHINA AND IF YOU
WANT TO GO BASICALLY PURELY U.S.
AND MGM IS THE WAY TO PLAY THAT
AND THAT HASN'T RUN AS MUCH AS
LAS VEGAS AND YOU WANT TO GO
THAT WAY, AS WELL AND THE WHOLE
SPACE SETS UP WELL HERE.
DOES THIS FALL INTO THE PLAY
THAT IF YOU WANT TO PLAY CHINA,
PLAY CHINA
>> BACK TO YOU
>> CASINOS ARE USING
DISCRETIONARY THAN GAMBLING, BUT
I DO LIKE THE CHINA ASPECT OF
IT, BUT AGAIN IF I WANT TO
INVEST IN THE CHINA GROWTH STORY
I WOULD RATHER INVEST IN CHINA.
>> WAN PECANOPY GROWTH AND IT IR
A DEAL TO BUY ACREAGE HOLDINGS
AS SOON AS TOMORROW.
WE'LL BRING YOU THE DETAILS
AFTER THIS BREAK AND THE DOW
STOCK BETTING AT AN ALL-TIME
HIGH AND WE'LL GIVE YOU THE NAME
AND TELL YOU WHAT HAS THEM SO
BEARISH.
Really?
[horn honks]
Man this is what I feel like
when I wear regular shoes,
cramped and uncomfortable.
We can arrange a little upgrade.
Which is why I wear Skechers...
Wide Fit shoes.
They have extra room throughout.
They're like a luxury
ride for my feet.
Try Skechers
Wide Fit shoes.
They're like a luxury
ride for my feet.
You should be mad that this is
your daily commute.
You should be mad at people who
forget they're in public.
And you should be mad
at simple things that are
unnecessarily complicated.
But you're not mad,
because you're trading
with E*TRADE,
which isn't complicated.
Their app makes trading
quick and simple
so you can strike
when the time is right.
Don't get mad,
get E*TRADE and start
trading today.
>>> THE STOCK YOU SEE THERE
JUMPING IN THE AFTER-HOURS
SESSION AND THIS ADDS TO THE
FLURRY OF DEALS AND IT IS WEED
WEEK AND WE'LL KEEP THE GOOD
TIMES ROLLING AND HE IS NOT ONLY
AN HEIR TO THE JIM BEAM BOURBON
FORTUNE AND THE BOOMING CANNABIS
COMPANY AND GREEN THUMB
INDUSTRIES AND THANK YOU FOR
BEING WITH US.
>> WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS ON
THIS DEAL AND THIS IS A GREAT
DAY FOR THE MULTI-STATE
OPERATORS AND THE ARGUMENT WAS
THAT THEY TRADING AT A DISCOUNT
TO THE CANADIAN COUSINS AND IT
LIMITS THEIR OPTIONS
>> YEAH.
THIS ONLY REINFORCES WHAT WE'VE
BEEN TALKING ABOUT FOR SO LONG
THAT THE OPPORTUNITY IN CANNABIS
IS HERE IN THE U.S. AND THIS IS
WHERE THE MARKET IS.
THIS IS A $50 TO $80 BILLION
INDUSTRY WHERE TOTAL MARKET
CAPITALIZATION IS STILL UNDER 15
BILLION.
SO IT'S A REALLY EXCITING TIME
AND THE U.S. IS WHERE THE
OPERATORS WANT TO BE AND IT'S
NOT ONLY CANADIAN OPERATORS AND
IT'S FOOD AND BEVERAGE, TOBACCO,
CPB BUSINESSES STUDDYING THE
SPACE.
>> SO BASICALLY, THEY WILL FIND
A WAY TO GET AROUND THE
RESTRICTIONS ON THEIR BUSINESS
AND INVESTING IN A FEDERALLY
ILLEGAL BUSINESS IS WHAT YOU'RE
THINKING
>> EVERYBODY IS STUDYING IT.
IN ORDER TO HAVE SUCCESS YOU
HAVE TO HAVE THE COST OF CAPITAL
AND WE BUILT A BUSINESS IN U.S.
IN LIMITED ACROSS THE COUNTRY
WHERE EVERYONE WAS RESTRICTED
AND THE TIDE IS CHANGING AND
IT'S QUITE AN EXCITING TIME.
>> YOU LOOK AT THIS DEAL IN THE
SPACE AND WHAT IT MEANS FOR YOU
AND YOU SEE CONSTELLATION HAVING
A STAKE IN CANOPY AND CANOPY
BUYING A MULTI-STATE OPERATOR
AND DO YOU THINK NOW THAT YOUR
OPTIONS IN TERMS OF WHO YOU
MIGHT COMBINE WITH DOWN THE ROAD
WILL EITHER BE SOONER OR LATER
HAS ACTUALLY WIDENED
>> WE HAVE TO SEE WHAT THE
DETAILS OF THIS DEAL ARE AND
EXACTLY HOW IT'S STRUCTURED AND
WHAT IT MEANS FOR SHAREHOLDERS
AND WHAT IT MEANS FOR BUSINESS
ANDTHE WAY WE LOOK AT THINGS I
THROUGH OUR LENS AND WHAT'S BEST
FOR OUR SHAREHOLDERS AND HOW WE
CREATE VALUE AND I WOULD BE
INTERESTED TO STUDY THE DETAILS
OF THIS.
>> HAVE YOU BEEN APPROACHED BY
CANOPY.
>> WE ARE TALKING TO PEOPLE IN
ALL SECTORS AND THE PHONE RINS A
LOT BECAUSE THERE IS WHERE THE
OPPORTUNITY IS
>> IN TERMS OF WHERE YOU THINK
IT'S MOST PROMISING AND THEY'RE
OPENING UP SOME SORT OF LEGAL
RECREATIONAL OR MEDICAL.
FOR INSTANCE, JUST BECAUSE NEW
YORK MIGHT LEGALIZE RECREATIONAL
AND IT MIGHT NOT BE A MARKET
THAT COULD BE PROFITABLE FOR
YOU?
>> WE SPENT A LOT OF TIME
STUDYING IT AND BUILT THE
BUSINESS FIVE YEARS AGO STARTING
IN ILLINOIS, NEVADA,
MASSACHUSETTS AND PENNSYLVANIA,
OHIO, NEW JERSEY, CONNECTICUT
ALL OF WHICH ARE STUDYING AND
FIGURING OUT HOW TO LEGALIZE TAX
AND REGULATE AND FUNDAMENTALLY
IN THE U.S. CANNABIS STANDS IN
THE CROSS SECTION OF THE OPIOID
EPIDEMIC THAT IS KILLING PEOPLE
AND CANNABIS OFFERS RELIEF FOR
THAT AND U.S. STATES THAT ARE
BANKRUPT AND NEED REVENUE AND
CANNABIS IS AN OPPORTUNITY FOR
MONSTROUS TAX REVENUE.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT CASE IS
REALLY BEING BORNE OUT IN THAT
CALIFORNIA, FOR INSTANCE, LAST
YEAR THE AMOUNT OF STATE TAX
REVENUE BROUGHT IN FROM CANNABIS
WAS ABOUT A THIRD OF WHAT HAD
BEEN PROJECTED AND THAT THERE'S
ACTUALLY SO MUCH COMPETITION
FROM THE BLACK MARKET WHICH
DOESN'T HAVE TO PAY OVERHEAD AND
DOESN'T PAY TAXES OR ANYTHING
LIKE THAT THAT IT'S DIFFICULT
FOR THESE BUSINESSES TO THRIVE
AND TO GENERATE THE TAX REVENUE
THAT STATES WANTED TO HAVE
>> SO CALIFORNIA IS AN ANOMALY
AND THE OLDEST AND BIGGEST
MARKET AND IF YOU LOOK AT NEVADA
WITH OVER 100 MILLION AND YOU'RE
ABOUT TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS IN
MASSACHUSETTS AS IT TAKES OVER
AND THE DOLLARS ARE VERY REAL
AND WE'RE ABLE TO BUILD SCHOOLS
AND HELP COMMUNITIES
>> HOW IMPORTANT IS CAPITAL AT
THIS POINT
CAPITAL IS DIFFICULT TO COME BY
FOR THIS INDUSTRY AT THIS POINT.
HOW IMPORTANT IS CAPITAL IN
TERMS OF BEING ABLE TO BUY THE
LICENSES IN THE STATES THAT OPEN
UP
>> PART OF YOU ARE WORK IS TO
WIN THE LICENSES IN A
COMPETITIVE PROCESS, FOR
EXAMPLE, NEW JERSEY HAD 146
APPLICANTS AND WE FINISHED
SECOND
WE WERE ABLE TO WIN A LICENSE
THAT'S MOST ACCRETIVE TO
SHAREHOLDERS AND WE'RE STUDYING
THE MARKET FOR LICENSES AND IT'S
AN EXCITING OPPORTUNITY BECAUSE
WE GET SYNERGIES IN ACQUISITION.
>> I'M ASKING THIS IN A BROADER
SENSE IN THAT THIS DEAL WILL
THEORETICALLY HIGHLIGHT THE
VALUE OR THE DISCOUNT THAT
MULTI-STATE OPERATORS WERE
TRADING AT VERSUS CANADIAN
COMPANIES.
>> WE WENT PUBLIC A YEAR AGO ON
THAT DISCOUNT KNOWING THE
OPPORTUNITY IS HERE.
I THINK TOMORROW IS ANOTHER STEP
ALONG THE WAY OF THE U.S.
INVESTOR STARTING TO COULD THAT
THE OPPORTUNITY USING U.S. MSOs
LISTED IN CANADA AND THIS IS
WHERE THE OPPORTUNITY IS AND I
THINK YOU SEE CONTINUED INTEREST
IN THE SPACE.
>> IS YOUR PHONE RINGING AS WE
SPEAK?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> NOT YET
>> THANKS FOR JOINING US
BEN COBLER OF GTI, GREEN THUMB
INDUSTRIES.
>> CONSTELLATION BRANDS.
YOU GET THE STOCK THAT TROUGHED
LATE LAST YEAR AND EARLIER THIS
YEAR AND IT'S BEEN OFF TO THE
RACES SINCE.
I'M NOT SUGGESTING IT'S THEIR
INVESTMENT IN THE INDUSTRY AND
IT HAS SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT
CLEARLY.
TO BEN'S POINT THERE ARE SO MANY
INDUSTRIES THAT WILL BE
DISRUPTED AND WE TALKED ABOUT
COSMETICS AND SPIRITS AND BEER
AND IT'S NOT GOING AWAY ANY TIME
SOON.
>> YEAH, JUST LOOK AT THE SECTOR
IN GENERAL
I THINK YOU GET THE VALUATIONS
MUCH HIGHER BECAUSE THIS COULD
SPARK A REALLY BIG RALLY
ALL RIGHT.
BY THE WAY, WE'LL HAVE MUCH MORE
ON THE BIG CANOPY DEAL TOMORROW.
I'LL BE SPEAKING WITH THE CEO OF
CANOPY GROWTH BRUCE LINTON AND
KEVIN MURPHY, SQUAWK BOX AT 6:50
A.M. WE'LL HAVE THE DETAILS OF
THE DEAL THEN.
COMING UP, THIS STOCK IS TRADING
AT AN ALL-TIME HIGH AND THIS DOW
STUD COULD TURN INTO A DUD
SEE WHAT WE DID THERE?
STUD INTO THE A DUD?
>> WE ARE LIVE AT NEW YORK
CITY'S TIMES SQUARE.
MUCH MORE FAST MONEY AHEAD
It will never
survive the winter.
Charging stations?
Good luck finding one of those.
So, maybe an electric car
isn't for you after all.
Or, is it?
♪
Does your Wealth Manager
measure up?
A CFA Charterholder does.
You've worked hard
to grow your wealth.
Make sure you're working
with a Wealth Manager
who can grow with you.
CFA Charterholders have
the investment expertise
to unlock opportunities other
advisors might not see.
Learn what a CFA Charterholdr
can do for you
at therightquestion.org
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "FAST
MONEY," A SHAKE-UP AT J.P.
MORGAN
MARIANNE LAKE WILL STEP DOWN AND
MOVE ON TO BECOME CEO OF
CONSUMER LENDING
THERE'S SPECULATION THAT SHE
COULD BE THE SUCCESSOR TO JAMIE
DIMON.
HOW DO YOU READ THESE MOVES?
>> I READ THIS AS THIS PUTS HER
IN POTENTIALLY THE POLE POSITION
FOR THAT
I THINK THAT SHE'S THE CFO, BUT
PEOPLE SAY, ALL RIGHT, SHE'S HAD
OPERATING EXPERIENCE AND THIS, I
THINK, WOULD REALLY GIVE HER
THAT
IT ALSO CERTAINLY MAKES ONE
WONDER WITH WELLS FARGO LOOKING
FOR A CEO, DID THEY COME KNOCK
ON HER DOOR?
THAT WOULD AREN'T BE SHOCKING TO
ANYONE, AND J.P. MORGAN THINKS
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE TO SOLIDIFY
OUR SUCCESSION PLAN EACH THOUGH
I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG JAMIE WILL
BE THERE
I THINK HE'S FANTASTIC, OF
COURSE, AND AT SOME POINT JAMIE
WILL LEAVE AND IT ALSO MAKES YOU
WONDER, ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ABOUT GORDON SMITH?
VERY TALENTED AND SHE'S, I
THINK, LATE 40s AND SHE'S LATE
50s AND JAMIE, I THINK IS EARLY
60s.
SO IT WOULDN'T BE SHOCKING TO
SEE HER BEING SET UP TO BE THE
NEXT CEO
>> YEAH.
THAT WAS -- I ALWAYS THOUGHT --
I THOUGHT FOR A WHILE IT WOULD
BE --
>> AND YOU WONDER IF TIM SLOAN
DIDN'T STEP DOWN IF ALL OF THIS
HADN'T BEEN IN THE WORKS ANYWAY.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> LET'S STICK WITH FINANCIALS
AND AMERICAN EXPRESS SHARES UP
20% AND OUTPERFORMING THE REST
OF THE SHARES AND THE RALLY
COULD COME TO AN END AND MIKE KO
IS HERE WITH THE OPTIONS ACTION.
HI, MIKE
>> THE OPTIONS MARKET IS
IMPLYING ABOUT A 3% MOVE FOR
AMERICAN EXPRESS AND THAT'S
ABOUT IN LINE WITH WHAT IT'S
AVERAGED OVER THE PAST EIGHT
QUARTERS AND WHEN I LOOKED AT
THE OPTIONS ACTIVITY AROUND AN
HOUR AND A HALF BEFORE THE
MARKET CLOSED AND IT HAD TRADED
TWO AND A HALF TIMES THE AVERAGE
DAILY VOLUME BY THE TIME THE
MARKET CLOSED AND THEREFORE
TRADING QUITE A LOT AS THE
CLOSING BELL APPROACHED AND MOST
OF THAT ACTIVITY WAS
CONCENTRATED IN THE 111 AND 107
PUTS THAT EXPIRE TOMORROW AND
THE REASON FOR THAT WAS THAT IT
WAS ACTUALLY PURCHASES OF THE
111, 107 PUT SPREAD INCLUDING A
BLOCK OF A THOUSAND OF THOSE
TRADING FOR 113.
AND THAT'S REPRESENTING 1% OF
THE CURRENT STOCK PRICE AND IT
WILL FALL AS LOW AS 107 AFTER
THEY REPORT TOMORROW
>> THANKS FOR THAT, MIKE
>> WE ARE OFF THIS FRIDAY, BUT
OPTIONS ACTION IS UP NEXT, AND
WONDER WHY GUY ADAMI IWANG
THIS UNICORN ONESIE?
IT'S NOT JUST WHAT HE WEARS
AROUND THE HOUSE
WE'LL TELL YOU AFTER THIS.
I don't know what's going on.
I've done all sorts of research,
read earnings reports,
looked at chart patterns.
I've even built my own
historic trading model.
And you're still not sure if you
want to make the trade?
Exactly.
Sounds like a case of
analysis paralysis.
Is there a cure?
TD Ameritrade's trade desk.
They can help gut check
your strategies
and answer all your
toughest questions.
Sounds perfect.
See, your stress level was here
and I got you down to here,
I've done my job.
Call for a Strategy Gut Check
with TD Ameritrade.
♪♪
- I love my Grandma.
- ANNCR: As you grow older,
your brain naturally
begins to change which may
cause trouble with recall.
- Learning from him is great...
when I can keep up!
- ANNCR: Thankfully,
Prevagen helps your brain
and improves memory.
- Dad's got all the answers.
- ANNCR: Prevagen is now
the number-one-selling
brain health supplement
in drug stores nationwide.
- She outsmarts me
every single time.
- Checkmate!
You wanna play again?
- ANNCR: Prevagen.
Healthier Brain. Better Life.
Oh, sir. That was my grandma's.
Don't worry, ma'am. All of your
stuff is in OK hands.
Just OK?
They don't give two and a half
stars to just anybody.
Here you go.
What's this?
It's your piano.
Hold this for a sec!
We don't have a piano.
No.
But the neighbors do.
Just OK is not OK.
Especially when it comes to you
network.
AT&T is America's best wireless
network
according to America's biggest
test.
Now with 5G Evolution.
The First Step to 5G.
More for your thing.
That's our thing.
>> WELCOME BACK TO FAST MONEY.
WE HAVE SOME BREAKING SNOOZE FOR
YOU.
EARLIER WE SPOKE TO THE CEO OF
CASPER, AND GUY ADAMI DID
UNDERCOVER WORK TO TEST OUT THE
LATET CASPER MATTRESS.
♪
>> MEL, WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT
IPOs FOR THE LAST MONTH, IT
SEEM, AND THE BUZZ WORD HAS BEEN
UNICORNS, BUT AS IT TURNS OUT
SOME UNICORNS COME IN A BOX.
WE'RE GOING TO FIND OUT IF THE
CASPER MATTRESS IS WHAT DREAMS
ARE MADE OF OR IF IT'S A
NIGHTMARE IN THE MAKING.
LET'S GO
♪
>> ALL RIGHT
ENOUGH GOOFING AROUND.
>> THAT WAS INCREDIBLY EASY.
>> DELIVERY SET UP AND ALL
THAT'S LEFT IS TO GET THE BED
MADE AND PUT ON MY PAJAMAS
DON'T JUDGE, BUT I'M
COMFORTABLE.
NOW IT'S TIME TO TEST THIS OUT
LET'S GET SOME REST.
♪
>> LIGHTS OUT.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE TO
BEGIN.
ONCE AGAIN, YOU'VE BEEN KICKED
OUT OF THE ROOM.
>> RIGHT
>> AND RELEGATED TO MY
DAUGHTER'S ROOM.
FANTASTIC THOUGH, WASN'T IT?
ISN'T THAT AMAZING
OF ALL OF THE RIDICULOUS THINGS
I'VE DONE OVER THE YEARS, THAT'S
THE MOST RIDICULOUS BY FAR, BUT
THIS IS WHEN IT'S TOO LIGHT OUT
AND YOU JUST NUT AND --?
I LIKE THE EYELASHES ON THERE.
>> YOU SHOULD GO PUBLIC.
YOU'RE A UNICORN
FINAL TRADE TIME
BRIAN KELLY.
>> OH, FOR ME?
TLT, BE DEFENSIVE IN THIS
MARKET
>> DAN SUZUKI.
>> HEALTH CARE, PROFITS ARE
SLOWING AND A GOOD TIME TO OWN
IT'S CHEAP AND THE BEST
LONG-TERM PERFORMING SECTORS OUT
THERE.
>> KAREN FINERMAN.
>> WHAT HE SAID AND WITH MORE
SPECIFICITY.
ANTHEM CALLS
>> UNICORN GUY
>> I HAVE TO THANK -- THE CRACK
STAFF, KELLY CAME TO THE HOUSE
AND SHE BROUGH