- Deal!
- Deal. You're taking $70.
Her case had the penny!
The penny was there.
Open your case.
Tony Oriente could not find
the end of the rainbow
and is leaving with $70.
I'm certain that this won't
dampen the light
that Tony brings
anywhere he goes.
That's it for us.
We'll see you next time
right here
on "Deal or No Deal."
>> Tonight on
"Jay Leno's Garage"...
>> Show me what you got!
>> We talk about what I took up
in school...
space.
This is called Scarecrow.
>> Because it doesn't
have a brain.
>> It's influenced car design,
technology, and our imagination.
It was a car I dreamed about
when I was 15 years old.
But is space the final frontier
for cars?
>> Yes! Yes.
>> To find out, astrophysicist
Neil deGrasse Tyson and I
get an education in going fast.
[screams]
[laughter]
Like, three times
the speed of sound, fast.
>> You've got a mean
fighting machine.
>> Pop culture historian
Charles Phoenix gives me
a tour of mid-century
atomic age design.
>> It is the epitome
of Space Age style.
>> We'll play America's
favorite car game with
well-known space expert,
Tim Allen.
I can't punch you in the face.
>> You could if you really
wanted to.
>> I do really want to.
I'll get behind the controls
of the most sophisticated
vehicle I've ever driven.
Oh, no! That can't happen.
NASA's $2.5 billion Mars Rover.
[cheering]
'Cause tonight, it's all about
astronomical speeds,
cosmic designs,
and stellar characters.
So gear up, 'cause this episode
is gonna be out of this world.
I'm coming for you!
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[rock music]
I'm on a lonely road in the
middle of the California desert.
The car I'm driving,
a 1969 Corvette.
[cash register bell rings]
But not just any Corvette,
this Corvette was owned
by Alan Bean,
fourth man to walk
on the Moon.
Back in the '60s, General Motors
had a program where
the astronauts could lease
a brand-new Corvette
for a dollar a year,
and all of them took
advantage of it.
But three of the astronauts,
Dick Gordon, Charles Conrad,
and Alan Bean, the owner
of this car,
wanted very special Corvettes.
Theirs were gold with the black
with a 427 engine,
a 4-speed transmission.
One of the most powerful
Corvettes you could buy.
On this episode, we're gonna
show the link between
space and automobiles.
The '50s and '60s was an
incredible time for scientific
progress.
>> We choose to go to the Moon
in this decade
and do the other things,
not because they are easy,
but because they are hard.
>> But it also made its way
into our everyday lives.
From the way we travel,
to architecture,
even the way we dress.
But most importantly for us,
the Space Age influenced
the automobile
through technology, design,
and speed.
We're on our way now
to Edwards Air Force Base,
and we're gonna talk to a man
who knows a lot about what it
takes to go fast.
I mean really fast.
[lively music]
♪ ♪
>> Jay. [laughs]
>> Hey, how you doing?
>> Where'd you steal this thing?
>> Isn't it cool?
>> [laughs]
>> It's Dr. Neil deGrasse Tyson,
world-renowned astrophysicist.
You know, this guy's won
numerous awards,
but to me, the coolest thing is
he's brought astrophysics
to the average person.
He explains space better than
anybody I've ever met.
Is this what you came in?
Did you break down?
>> Yeah, I-- [laughs]
Yeah, you know, just cars
are not good enough for me.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, the SR-71.
>> This plane is actually quite
old, isn't it?
>> Yeah, well, I think it dates
back from the '50s, early '60s.
>> The SR-71 was essentially
a spy plane
that was designed to operate
at high speeds and altitudes,
making it almost invisible.
And in its 25 years of service,
an estimated 4,000 missiles
were fired at it,
and not a single one
hit its target.
>> What intrigues me about
the SR-71 is they had to
design it to be most efficient
at the Mach 3 speeds
it was hitting.
>> Right.
>> And at Mach 3,
air is going rapidly
over the skin of the plane.
>> Right.
>> And there's friction,
there are shock waves
transmitting energy
in the form of heat,
blowing air on top of it.
>> So is the plane hotter
than the air?
>> So here's what happens.
Here's air.
>> Yeah.
>> And you're moving rapidly
through it, you rapidly compress
the air.
>> Right.
>> That will raise
the temperature of the air.
>> I see, I got you, I got you.
>> That's what's happening.
If the air just slowly
goes out of your way
as you go through it--
>> Okay.
>> When you walk through
the air--
>> Right.
>> You're not--
>> And is that how you
walk through the air like that?
Is that how you--
When you're alone and there's
nobody around, is that how
you walk through the air?
>> When I'm not going fast
through the air--
>> Right, right, okay.
And I'm not passing judgment.
That's fine with me.
>> Well, the air parts for me.
>> The air parts for you.
>> Yes, yes, okay.
So the cool thing about this is
you fill it with fuel...
>> Right.
>> But on the ground,
the fuel would just drip.
Why? Because the seals
of the plane are not yet closed.
>> Well they need heat to close.
>> Yes! Yes.
So the plane is designed
to exist at a much higher
temperature when it's going
Mach 2, Mach 3.
Then the heat gets transmitted
to the fuselage,
the fuselage expands,
all the seals close--
>> Right.
>> And now you've got a mean
fighting machine.
>> Let's go inside.
>> Yeah.
Love me some airplane museums.
>> Wow, a lot of history here.
Now the cool part is,
this is stuff most folks
don't usually get to see.
But the people at Edwards
have opened up a few doors
for us, and we're gonna
take a look at the history
of speed.
That's the one that broke
the sound barrier.
>> Right. You can see the design
is very different from
all of those, sort of,
World War II airplanes
that have rounded noses.
>> The aerodynamic design
of this plane not only helped
Chuck Yeager break
the sound barrier,
it also influenced car design
and technology forever.
>> Here we got the engine
that was actually in the X-15.
>> So it went at
249,000 feet.
So they were essentially
astronauts, weren't they?
>> Yeah, essentially,
and all the early generations
of astronauts you had,
you know, flight time in this.
>> Right.
So did you ever want to be
an astronaut?
>> No, I never did.
I knew early on that
I loved astrophysics.
So, the large-scale universe.
And there was NASA going into,
like, low Earth orbit.
>> Right.
>> And maybe to the Moon
and back, but to me,
that was such a small part
of the universe at large,
that, to me, that wasn't really
going into space.
>> Yeah. See, I knew
I wanted to be an astronaut.
I flew with
the Blue Angels once.
>> Oh, okay.
>> And you realize these guys
are smarter than you,
can do math better than you,
can do more push-ups than you--
>> [laughs] Push-ups.
>> Uh--
>> Okay, but that's not why
I didn't--I wasn't--
>> I'm sure that's why--
I'm sure could have passed
the physical when you walked in
like this.
I'm sure that would have--
When you split the air
like this...
Okay, I like museums
as much as the next guy,
but you know, I think it's time
to meet the real deal.
>> Hello.
>> Hi.
>> Hello, hello.
>> Madam Secretary.
>> Hello there.
>> It's a pleasure. Neil Tyson.
>> Debbie James, so nice
to meet you, Neil.
>> Deborah Lee James is the 23rd
Secretary of the Air Force,
and only the second woman
to hold this position.
She oversees over 600,000
airmen and women,
as well as the Air Force's
annual budget of $139 billion.
>> Welcome to Edwards
and welcome to the most advanced
aircraft in our inventory,
the F-22.
>> We'll be the judge of that.
[laughter]
>> The F-22 Raptor is the most
intelligent jet fighter
in the world.
It's loud,
incredibly intimidating,
and has a cruising speed of
just over 1,200 miles an hour.
And if its design
looks familiar,
that's because most super cars,
hyper cars, whatever you want
to call them,
all take influence
from this aircraft.
And what is the flying speed?
>> So it's a Mach 2
class airplane, which means
it can go approximately
twice the speed of sound.
The airplane is capable of going
much faster than that,
but there's limitations
as far as actually
skin temperature.
Airplane gets too hot
if it goes too fast.
>> First rule of combat,
don't vaporize your pilot.
>> Exactly.
>> Right. They hate it when
you do that.
>> They hate every time
it happens.
>> The other cool thing
about this aircraft is
it's highly stealthy,
which means it's nearly
invisible to what could be
enemy radar.
>> Now where does it fire from?
Is this a bomber, primarily?
>> This is primarily
an air-to-air fighter
with an air-to-ground role.
You can see, this is the doors
for one of the side weapon bays.
>> Okay.
>> There's a total of two
side weapon bays,
which can fit one missile each.
Two underwing bays, which can
fit three missiles each.
>> The engines are way
back here.
How many cubic feet of air
goes through there every minute?
Do you know?
>> Just say a bajillion.
>> A bajillion?
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> A lot.
>> Are there manual controls
to any of this, or is it
all electronic?
>> It's all electronic.
>> Okay.
>> Will the computer ever judge
that the pilot's crazy?
We're not doing that--[laughs]
We're not following
that instruction.
>> Yes, it's self--
[booming]
>> [screams]
[laughter]
>> That's a sonic boom.
>> That was a big sonic boom.
Okay--
>> That was a standard
sonic boom.
[laughter]
>> Okay, now you've seen
just how brave I am.
Let's head to the test stand,
where we can see this engine
in action.
Looks a lot bigger up close.
>> And Jay and Neil, I want
to introduce you to Triggs
from Pratt & Whitney.
>> Mike Triggs,
nice to meet you, Jay.
>> Triggs, as in trigonometry?
>> Oh, yes, sir.
>> The plural of trigonometry.
>> Yes sir, heard that
many times.
Welcome, welcome, nice to
meet you.
>> What would this be
in automotive horsepower?
I know you measure differently.
>> It's hard to convert.
I'm gonna say on the order
of 100,000.
Two of these side by side...
>> 100,000 horsepower?
>> Pushing the raptor.
It's almost a cruise ship
pushing an airplane
through the sky.
You guys wanna run it?
>> Yeah, let's run it.
>> Let's do it.
>> We'll go inside,
and then we'll crank it up.
If you're standing close
proximity to the engine
when it's up at maximum power,
it's putting so much
acoustic energy into the air
that you can feel it
in your internal organs.
>> Yeah.
And believe me, nobody wants
melted organs.
Fortunately, there's a special
insulated building where my
organs will be just fine.
>> All right, Jay.
>> Damn it, Jim, I'm a doctor.
>> [laughs]
Let's see what you got.
>> Let's see, let's bring it up.
Okay, now, there we go.
>> All right.
>> Now it's starting to sound--
here we go.
>> Now we're talking.
Yeah, 25, 30.
>> More, more, more.
[engine roaring]
>> Whoo!
>> There it is, there it is.
>> Look at that.
Hey, not my fuel.
Yeah--yes, it is, we're paying
for this fuel.
Let me bring it
all the way back.
What is that,
about 1,000 gallons of gas
we blew out of that thing?
>> Yeah.
>> Whoo-hoo! We gotta
get one of these.
[laughter]
Okay, that was pretty cool,
but I think it's time
to give the good doctor
a dramatic demonstration
of exactly what we're
talking about.
Can we use the runway
to take him for a ride?
You wanna go for a ride
in the jet car?
That sounds like a yes.
>> [mouthing silently]
>> Coming up...
Up to 165.
Can Neil deGrasse Tyson
handle the high speeds
of the jet car?
[window thuds]
Lost a window.
Hi, most people know me
for my award-winning comedy,
but I also used
to be a doctor.
It's just like most
people know State Farm
for home and
auto insurance.
We've also
won five J.D. Power
awards in a row
for life insurance.
Um...
I don't know how
you got those in
there, but uh...
I'm impressed.
Now what?
I don't know.
Life insurance
you didn't expect
from the company
you know you can trust.
State Farm.
When I book at Hilton.com
I get to select my room
from the floor plan...
Free Wi-Fi...
...and the Price
Match Guarantee.
So with Hilton
there is no catch.
Yeah the only catch
is I'm never leaving.
No I'm serious,
I live here now.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
Book at Hilton.com
♪Work so hard give it everything
you got♪
♪Strength of a lioness tough as
a knot♪
♪Rocking the stage and we're
never gonna stop♪
♪All Strength, No Sweat... just
in case you forgot♪
♪All Strength, No Sweat...♪
♪No No No Sweat...♪♪
After walking six miles at
an amusement park...
Bill's back needed a
vacation from his vacation.
So he stepped on the
Dr. Scholl's kiosk.
It recommends our best
Custom Fit Orthotic
to relieve foot, knee, or
lower back pain.
So you can move more.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to move.
♪♪
[elevator bell]
Yup.
Little choices make
a big difference.
Like delicious fruits
and veggies.
However You Healthy.
Naked.
GLAD YOU'RE BACK
HOW YOU FEELING?
♪ ♪ ♪
(BOTH) EXHAUSTED.
BUT FINALLY BEING ABLE TO MAKE
THAT VOLUNTEER TRIP HAPPEN
WAS... AWESOME.
AWESOME.
YOU HAVE TO SCRUB.
WHAT DO THEY...
THEY USE FOR WASHING.
♪ ♪ ♪
LET'S DO IT EVERY YEAR.
WE'LL DO IT EVERY YEAR.
I THOUGHT YOU'D SAY THAT -
LET'S DO IT.
♪ ♪ ♪
SEE HOW INVESTING WITH A J.P.
MORGAN ADVISOR CAN HELP YOU.
VISIT YOUR LOCAL CHASE BRANCH.
These folks,
they don't have time to
go to the Post Office
They have businesses to grow
Customers to care for
Lives to get home to
They use Stamps.com
Print discounted postage
for any letter
Any package
Any time
Right from your computer
All the amazing services
of the Post Office
only cheaper
Get our Special TV Offer
A 4 week trial
plus postage and
a digital scale
Go to Stamps.com/save and
never go to the Post Office
again
[upbeat music]
>> We've seen some amazing jets,
but those are ones that go
through the air.
[engine roaring]
How about a jet
that only goes on the ground?
Now have you ever been
in a truly homemade car?
>> Never.
>> Well you're gonna come
for a ride in the Leno.
I'm gonna take
Neil deGrasse Tyson
out in my car, the EcoJet.
Yeah.
>> This is the Leno.
>> Well, it's not the Leno,
but we call it the EcoJet.
But it uses a jet engine
that had belonged to a big
attack helicopter.
>> You made a car
with a jet engine?
>> This was something
I really wanted to do.
With the help of General Motors
and Honeywell,
we built a jet car that runs on
renewable energy.
Oh, and it goes
pretty fast, too.
[engines roaring]
What's the fastest you've ever--
[engine roars]
We are gonna go faster
than that guy.
I'm coming for you!
Your ass is mine!
[laughter]
>> And why is it called Eco?
'Cause this doesn't look
very eco to me.
>> Well actually,
it's called Eco 'cause when
we built this, we built it to
run on biofuel.
>> So it's got a jet engine,
where's the exhaust?
>> This is a shaft driven,
you understand?
>> Okay.
>> It turns a shaft,
which goes to the transmission,
which means it's at
the rear, here.
And then your exhaust heat
comes out the top.
In the helicopter--
>> It would've been way cooler
if flames came out the back of
the car, I'm just saying.
>> Well, yeah, I'm not
trying to scare children.
We're trying to make
a transportation vehicle here.
>> All right, I'm ready
to take a spin.
>> Let's do it.
>> All right.
[horn honks]
Let's do it!
[intense music]
♪ ♪
Show me what you got!
Whoo!
♪ ♪
>> 120.
[window thuds]
Lost a window.
[engine roaring]
[window thuds]
Oh, note to self...
Fix that driver's side window.
>> You're aerodynamic enough.
Doesn't matter.
♪ ♪
Whoo!
>> It's 160.
♪ ♪
Actually 165.
Well we got up to 165.
We had a window blow out
at 130.
Well that--that's gonna happen.
>> [laughs]
>> But that's a--
>> Stuff happens.
>> Yeah, stuff happens.
Stuff happens!
I mean, we can go a lot faster,
but I thought that was enough.
We don't want to kill
the good doctor.
>> [laughs]
I want a bumper sticker, too,
that says "My Other Car is
a Jet Engine."
>> Yeah, my other car
is a jet engine, I want--
We're gonna make a car guy
out of him yet.
Well now we're gonna go over to
what many consider
the unlikely birthplace
of the Space Age,
the Columbia Memorial
Space Center in Downey,
California.
You'll see how space travel
influenced Space Age style.
It really touched all aspects
of our lives, from fashion,
futuristic electronics,
mod design, home appliances,
even food.
>> Space Food Sticks,
they're compact, nutritious,
high energy food.
>> The Space Age really started
in the '50s, right after
World War II,
because jet planes had come in,
cars had all kinds of wild fins
and wild Jet Age styling.
Oh, here. Here you go.
Here's a perfect example
of what I'm talking about.
[funky rock music]
♪ ♪
[cash register bell rings]
This is a 1961
Pontiac Bonneville.
This is Charles Phoenix.
Charles, how are you, my friend?
>> How you doing, Jay?
>> Good to see you.
Now Charles is the man
when it comes to the 1950s
and '60s Americana.
He's a pop culture humorist
and a classic car
collector as well.
And there's no one I know
who appreciates Space Age style
more than this guy.
>> I love everything to do
with astronauts going to Mars,
going to the Moon and this.
Every time I see this,
I practically feel like
I have to run over and give it
a big hug.
>> Well, then--
>> I mean, it feels like
an old friend, don't you think?
>> Yeah, it does feel
like an old friend.
There you go.
All right.
I love the command module,
and you know, this really
goes perfectly with it.
I like a lot of
the Space Age goo-gahs
on this thing.
You know, the little gunsight
looking--are these to
aid parking, is that the idea?
>> You know what?
I think they're just supposed to
help guide your way no matter
where you're going.
>> Yeah. You can see
the rocket theme.
You see it there?
Where it turns into
Bonneville, here, and then
this looks like the thrusters
from a jet, coming out the back.
And this has kind of
a jet thing, too.
And then, you still have
the vestiges of a tailfin, here.
Just a--just a little bit.
>> That's kind of what I call
a finette.
>> both: A finette.
>> Yes, yes.
>> Why not? I also love the fact
they color coordinated
everything back then.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> It was like they were
selling fashion, you know?
>> As you can see,
very important.
Notice how I am not--
Well, I guess I am
color coordinated.
Kinda.
>> You ready to take it
for a roll?
>> Let's take it for a roll.
>> Here's the keys.
>> Let's do it.
>> The original keys, too.
>> Cool.
[light music]
♪ ♪
[engine turns over]
>> ♪ Da da da da da ♪
♪ Doo doo doo doo doo doo doo ♪
>> Jay, the Space Age is like
the mood is up,
the standard of living
is flying high,
and prosperity rules.
>> See, you were lucky.
You grew up here.
When you're living
in Massachusetts,
and you're sitting
in math class and it's freezing,
and you have a copy
of "Hot Rod Magazine"
under your math book--
Everything was happening
in Downey, Hermosa, Redondo.
There was surfing,
there was the hot rods,
the Beach Boys, I mean,
everything was here.
>> You know, Southern California
is a cultural juggernaut.
Downey, they call it
The Cradle of the Cosmic Age.
>> You know, just driving around
Southern California,
there's all sorts of little cues
to the Space Age.
Take a look.
>> Okay, Jay.
Hold on, this is major.
This is real, this is deep.
This is the oldest McDonald's
on the planet.
>> Wow.
When I worked at McDonald's,
their slogan was,
"Where a family of four can have
lunch for under a dollar."
There's Speedee Hamburger.
>> Even the name,
it's all about speed.
The Space Age.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Everything is going fast.
This one was built in 1953.
And as you can see, it is
a masterpiece of mid-century
modernity.
>> It was kinda Space Age
with the Golden Arch like that.
>> That rocket launcher
roofline, I love.
And don't you love
the red and white stripes?
It's a cultural juggernaut.
Paris has the Eiffel Tower.
Pisa has the Leaning Tower of.
>> Right.
>> And Downey has the oldest
McDonald's on the planet.
>> And you can't get a hamburger
at the Eiffel Tower.
>> You cannot get
a hamburger there.
I love all of the design
of the era, I mean, it was
the Tomorrowland era.
>> I remember Space Age kitchen.
>> Oh, yeah, no, I love
atomic kitchens.
>> Every woman is fascinated
by Frigidaire's
Kitchen of Tomorrow.
>> Right now, the question
before the house is:
What's cooking, and when
do we eat?
>> Wait till you see
this bowling alley sign, Jay.
>> Okay.
>> From about 1960,
it is the epitome
of Space Age style.
Oh, there it is.
I see it. [gasps]
Oh, God!
I mean, what makes this sign
really unique, I mean,
besides the B-O-W-L, Bowl,
for bowling alley,
letters that go up and down
like they're dancing...
>> Right, right.
>> Are not one, not two,
three, four, five, six, seven
starbursts.
>> Right.
>> I mean, this sign
is sparkling.
It's a masterpiece!
>> Looks like the Jetsons
would bowl there.
>> Exactly.
[light music]
♪ ♪
So right now, we are on our way
to Bob's Big Boy Broiler.
>> Right.
>> In Downey.
>> Okay.
>> Which is a juggernaut
of a landmark.
>> Another jugger--that's a lot
of juggernauts here.
>> Well, I'm just saying.
You know, I am really passionate
about this stuff.
♪ ♪
Well here we are, Jay,
the largest carhop restaurant
built in California, ever.
>> Really?
>> And--yeah, in its day,
it was the place to see
and be seen--
>> Yeah.
>> In your hot rod, custom
or classic cars.
And there is a car show
here tonight.
>> Actually, it's not
a car show, it's just a typical
night at Bob's Big Boy.
>> Yeah, that's it.
It's a typical night.
Everybody drives
vintage cars around here.
And I love it.
Doesn't get more authentic
than this.
Well it really wouldn't be
the true experience without
being served by a carhop.
Here they are.
>> Oh, here we are.
>> Here we go.
>> Wow.
>> Oh, cool, look at that.
>> And here's your Big Boy.
>> Enjoy, boys.
>> Thank you.
>> Why thank you very much.
>> Mmm.
>> This is the America I know.
>> This is Space Age
Americana right here.
A triple hamburger
in a classic car.
Bob's Big Boy Broiler.
>> Doesn't get any better
than this.
>> Cheers, Jay.
>> Coming up...
>> Ohh. Clever.
>> Tim Allen shows off
his car nerd knowledge.
>> '72.
>> '72 is correct.
And reveals a little too much
about himself.
Bondage, spanking.
>> Oh, very into that.
MOVING?
THAT'S HARDER NOW BECAUSE
OF PSORIATIC ARTHRITIS.
BUT YOU'RE STILL MOVED
BY MOMENTS LIKE THIS.
DON'T LET PSORIATIC
ARTHRITIS TAKE THEM AWAY.
TALTZ REDUCES JOINT
PAIN AND STIFFNESS
AND HELPS STOP THE
PROGRESSION OF JOINT DAMAGE.
FOR PEOPLE WITH MODERATE
TO SEVERE PSORIASIS,
90% SAW SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT.
TALTZ EVEN GIVES YOU A CHANCE
AT COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
DON'T USE IF YOU'RE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING, YOU SHOULD
BE CHECKED FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR
ABILITY TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR
DOCTOR IF YOU
HAVE AN
INFECTION,
SYMPTOMS,
OR RECEIVED A
VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INFLAMMATORY BOWEL DISEASE
CAN HAPPEN WITH TALTZ,
INCLUDING WORSENING OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
FOR ALL THE THINGS
THAT MOVE YOU.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
Just between us, cleaning with a
mop and bucket is such a hassle.
Well I switched to Swiffer Wet
Jet and it's awesome.
It's an all-in-one that absorbs
dirt and grime deep inside.
And it helps prevent streaks and
haze.
Stop Cleaning. Start Swiffering
You still stressed about buying
our first house, sweetie?
Yeah,
I thought doing some hibachi
grilling would help take
my mind off it all.
Maybe you could relieve
some stress by calling GEICO
for help with our
homeowners insurance.
GEICO helps with
homeowners insurance?
They sure do.
And they could save us
a bundle of money too.
I'm calling GEICO
right now.
Cell phone?
It's ringing.
Get to know GEICO and
see how much you could
save on homeowners and
condo insurance.
I had no symptoms
of Hepatitis C.
Mine...
Get to know GEICO and
see how much you could
...caused liver damage.
EPCLUSA treats all main types
of chronic Hep C.
Whatever your type,
ask your doctor
if EPCLUSA is your kind of cure.
I had the common type.
Mine was rare.
EPCLUSA has a 98%
overall cure rate.
I just found out
about my hepatitis C.
I knew for years.
EPCLUSA is only one
pill, once a day,
taken with or without
food for 12 weeks.
Before starting EPCLUSA,
your doctor will
test if you have had
hepatitis B, which may flare up
and could cause
serious liver problems
during and after treatment.
Tell your doctor if you
have had hepatitis B
other liver or
kidney problems, HIV
or other medical conditions...
...and all medicines you take,
including herbal supplements.
Taking amiodarone
with EPCLUSA may
cause a serious slowing
of your heart rate.
Common side effects include
headache and tiredness
Ask your doctor today, if
EPCLUSA is your kind of cure.
[funky music]
♪ ♪
>> It's time for another
episode of...
Welcome to another episode
of "Stump a Car Nerd."
This is where we take
a knowledgeable car enthusiast,
we blindfold them,
and they have to guess
what vehicle they're in.
Today we're talking
with Timothy Allen, is it?
>> What are you, my mother?
Nobody calls me Timothy.
>> Tim is an old buddy of mine.
Is that what it is?
You pushing me?
Oh yeah?
He's been on the show
a couple of times now.
You'll always be
the Tool Man, Allen.
>> You look like my wife
in that car.
>> Actually, he played
an astronaut in the movies,
so there is a tie-in here.
>> [laughs]
>> Let's put this blindfold on.
>> This is--shades of grey.
And I get no pants, right?
>> All right, go ahead,
you know.
>> Oh, this is creepy.
>> Okay, there we go.
>> Jay!
>> Okay, open the door.
>> I can smell it.
Now, wait, wait, which way
are we going?
All right.
>> Okay.
>> I don't wanna
bang into [bleep].
>> This is a 1970 Mazda Cosmo,
updated with a little
later engine.
This engine puts out about
225 horsepower, but it's
still a Wankel.
>> Where's--I need--
where's the rearview mirror?
>> I chose this car
'cause I'm pretty sure
I'm gonna stump Tim.
>> Ohh. Clever.
>> Let's put you in the vehicle.
>> So we're gonna
drive blindfolded.
There's a good idea.
>> Yeah, yeah, come on
over here.
>> It's California,
what difference does it make?
>> Watch your head.
>> Oh.
>> Ow!
>> All right, ready to
start it up?
[engine turns over]
That's a major clue.
>> Well, the major clue is this.
>> Right.
>> Have you ever eaten anything
blindfolded?
>> Yeah, you can't tell an apple
from a potato.
>> You can't--
but it's [bleep] weird.
>> Have you ever eaten
a blindfold?
That's the tough one.
>> [laughs]
>> Yeah, I mean,
that's really hard.
>> Tastes like an apple.
>> Oh, yeah.
[lively rock music]
♪ ♪
>> It's a multi-cam
four cylinder.
[buzzer blares]
>> No, not a multi-cam
four cylinder.
♪ ♪
>> It's a quick thing,
and it's not very new.
[bell dings]
It's Japanese.
>> It is Japanese.
>> Yes.
>> What made you say Japanese?
>> The mirror up front,
and the fact that it's
a right-hand drive.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm honing in on
Isuzu and Mazda.
>> Feel free to hone in on
whoever you like.
>> [laughs]
[engine revs]
I gotta say, this is
a Wankel engine.
>> It is a Wankel engine.
>> Yeah.
>> Are you ready to make
a guess?
[drum roll]
>> I gotta go with the Mazda.
[shimmering tones]
>> That's right,
it's a Mazda Cosmo.
>> [screams] God, it's bright!
>> There you go.
>> Is this yours?
>> Yeah.
>> Can I have it?
>> Isn't it smooth?
It just revs forever,
doesn't it?
>> Forever.
>> We have another vehicle.
Let's put on the blindfold.
>> This is so much fun.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
But I'm sure the money
will be rolling in.
>> All righty,
let's turn around.
>> Am I--am I turned around?
>> This is a 1959 Oldsmobile 88.
[cash register bell rings]
It has a 315 horsepower
rocket V8 engine,
a four-barrel carburetor.
>> Is it pricey?
Can I touch the thing,
or is it--
>> You can touch it, yes.
And has all kinds of
spaceship-like details.
This is perfect for
the mid-century man...
>> Definitely not European.
>> Who dreams of being
an astronaut.
You're not a young man anymore.
>> [laughs]
Why is there marijuana in here?
[engine turns over]
Safety first.
Put on the seatbelt.
>> Oh, I've got mine on.
That's the only one we need
to worry about.
>> [laughs]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
>> It's a GM product.
It's a V8.
[bell dings]
It's not shifting like a Ford.
>> What makes you think
it's not shifting like a Ford?
>> Ford's a little crispy.
It had better transmissions
in this era.
This is late '50s.
[bell dings]
>> Does it feel higher end
or lower end?
>> It feels higher end
than Chevy, judging by
the dashboard.
>> Okay.
>> And it's got a vent window.
A lot of bull[bleep] going on.
The curves and [bleep].
A lot of body, a lot of style.
Custom made stuff.
Doesn't come in Chevys.
>> How about the size?
Look, see, I can't punch you
in the face.
>> You could if you really
wanted to.
>> I do really want to.
>> All right, well--
>> Believe me, I want to
more than anything.
[laughter]
You ready to make a guess?
What do you got?
>> Let's say...
[drum roll]
'58 Oldsmobile 88.
>> Good! '59 Oldsmobile 88.
>> Get out!
>> Yeah, that's what it is.
♪ Longer, leaner, lower ♪
>> [laughs]
>> You've done well.
You've guessed both cars.
There's one left.
>> All right, here we go.
>> Let's put this on.
>> Let's get this going,
'cause CNBC's got financial data
to give people.
>> Let's open the door.
All right, come on in here.
Here we go.
This is a 1972 Citroen SM.
It's French, it's elegant,
and even though this car
is over 40 years old,
it still looks like
the future today.
>> Ohh.
Ohh.
That is peculiar.
Oh, big door.
Is there another door back here?
>> both: No.
>> So it's a two-door.
>> Only two doors.
>> Okay.
[engine turns over]
[rock music]
♪ ♪
Is it considered a sports model
in its day?
>> Sporty.
Not a sports car, per se.
>> Is it front drive?
[bell dings]
>> Front-wheel drive.
>> All right, now I got it down
to Citroen, Peugeot--
>> What made you think
it's French?
>> Um, seat bolsters,
the sound of the motor,
these weird door handles.
But these--definitely think
these--the seat--there's
too many seat mechanisms.
>> Yeah. What era do you think
this car is?
>> Oh, [bleep].
>> No, that's wrong.
>> [laughs]
Oh, God.
>> What era would you say?
>> Late '60s, early '70s.
>> Closer to which?
>> Early '70s.
>> Early '70s, good.
And what kind of motor
you think it is?
>> Six cylinder of some sort,
but it's--
>> Six cylinder. What do you
think, straight six? V6?
>> No, it's gotta be V6.
It revs pretty well.
It has a nice--
>> Okay.
>> It has a nice sound to it
when it gets up there.
>> All right, so, you ready
to make a guess?
>> And I'm gonna go Citroen.
>> Citroen is correct.
>> Whoa!
>> What year would you
say it is?
>> '72.
[bell dings]
>> '72 is correct.
What model do you think?
>> Um--
>> I'll give you a clue.
Uh, bondage, spanking--
>> Oh, very into that.
>> Yeah, okay.
The letters are an abbreviation
for what many, but not you,
would consider deviant behavior.
>> [laughs]
SM.
>> SM, now--so give me
the whole thing.
It's a what?
>> A 1972 Citroen SM.
>> Yes! That is correct!
You may remove the blindfold.
>> Yes.
>> That's very good.
Tim, three for three.
Very good.
We'll just step on the gas
and pull away. [laughs]
Coming up...
We'll meet the incredible team
behind the most expensive
vehicle ever made.
>> Bam, you hit the side
of a rock and fall over.
The mission's over.
>> And guess what.
They let me drive it.
Well, I mean, kind of, sort of.
When you book at Hilton.com,
you get the Price
Match Guarantee.
So if you find your
room at a lower rate,
Hilton is like...
We're gonna match that rate
and give you an extra 25% off.
What would travel sites do if
you found a different price?
That's not my problem,
it's your problem.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
♪ I'm tasting olives... ♪
♪ Roasted pine nuts... ♪
♪ Mmm this red pepper... ♪
♪ That's spicy stuff... ♪
Fresh flavor. Feel good food.
Sabra Hummus.
♪ I just had Sabra Hummus and
now I feel good! ♪
When did you see the sign?
When I needed to create a better
visitor experience.
Improve our workflow.
Attract new customers.
That's when FASTSIGNS
recommended fleet graphics.
Yeah, and now business
is rolling in.
Get started at fastsigns.com.
(Dad) Got it?
(Boy) Got it.
NOOOOOOO...
(Dad) NOOOOOOO...
(VO) Quick, the Quicker
Picker Upper!
Bounty picks up messes quicker
and is two times more absorbent.
Bounty, the Quicker
Picker Upper.
The Lexus ES.
Every curve, every
innovation, every feeling.
A product of mastery.
Lease the 2019 ES 350 for
$389 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
Minimums and fees.
They seem to be the
very foundation of
your typical bank.
Capital One is
anything but typical.
That's why We designed
Capital One Cafes.
You can get savings and
checking accounts with
no fees or minimums.
AND one of America's
best savings rates.
To top it off,
you can open one from
anywhere in 5 minutes.
This isn't a typical bank.
This is Banking Reimagined.
What's in your wallet?
(Engine revving)
( ♪♪ )
(Soft beeps)
Little choices make
a big difference.
Like nutritious
fruit smoothies.
However You Healthy.
Naked.
[lively music]
♪ ♪
>> The car I'm driving right now
is called the Rocket.
It was designed back in
the early '90s by Gordon Murray,
the famous designer,
responsible for so many F1 wins,
and of course, the iconic
McLaren F1,
one of the greatest cars
of the 20th century.
Gordon Murray's design was all
about power-to-weight ratio.
This car has a Yamaha motorcycle
Genesis engine, that makes
147 horsepower,
but only weighs 775 pounds.
And the best part is...
[engine roars]
It's street legal!
What does it have to do
with the Space Age?
Well, it's called the Rocket
because it goes like a rocket.
[engine roars]
Right now, we're on our way
to NASA's Jet Propulsion
Laboratory, which is just
15 miles from my garage.
Home to incredible robotics,
powerful telescopes,
and of course, the $2.5 billion
Mars Rover, and the crew
that built it.
Dr. Elachi, how are you, sir?
>> Hi, Jay. How are you doing?
>> Oh, what an honor this is.
>> Welcome to JPL.
>> This is where it all happens.
I mean, this goes back to
the very beginning
of space flight in America,
this whole complex, doesn't it?
>> Yeah, yeah.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
>> Wow.
How cool is this?
I had seen this room
on television.
I never thought I'd actually be
standing in it.
>> So as you look at
this screen, as we speak,
we have 22 spacecrafts in space,
all across the solar system.
This is Jim, who's in charge...
>> Jim, how are you, sir?
>> Very well, nice to
meet you, Jay.
>> You too.
>> Jim is going to be
giving you the detail.
>> Doctor, thank you.
>> Take care.
>> I'll see you, Charles.
>> Someone made the analogy
this is like
NASA's steering wheel.
>> I think you could say that.
>> Yeah.
>> For deep space missions.
>> Right.
>> And for Earth science
missions as well.
We operate many of the vehicles
from this room in fact.
>> That's the room you guys are
in on August 5th--was it 2012?
>> That's the date,
that's right.
>> When Curiosity landed.
After a seven-month-long
journey,
the Mars Rover Curiosity
made its final descent
onto the planet Mars.
And at $2.5 billion,
it's by far the most expensive
and advanced Rover yet.
Landing this craft without
flipping it, crashing it,
or breaking it
was the challenge.
[cheers and applause]
>> How emotional a moment
was that?
>> That was extremely emotional.
I've been here for over 28 years
and that was probably the most
emotional evening of my life.
>> Yeah, I mean, that's such
an amazing thing to me,
to have so much time and energy
invested in one critical
little moment.
>> With the world watching.
>> Yeah.
>> We had over 50 million
Americans watching us just on
our web servers in that room
that night.
>> Yeah, yeah, wow.
>> That's a lot of pressure
for us geeks and nerds,
if you will.
>> Yeah, I'd love to have
50 million Americans watching.
>> Right?
♪ ♪
>> Well now you're gonna see
the most expensive vehicle
on the planet.
[knocking]
And the amazing thing is,
it's housed in
an ordinary garage.
Literally.
Just like a garage
you'd have at home.
>> Hi, Jay.
>> John, how are you?
>> Good, how you doing?
Welcome to the Mars Yard.
>> Thank you, thank you.
And this is the Mars Rover,
isn't it?
>> This is it. This is
what we call the VSTB,
Vehicle Systems Test Bed,
and it basically is
the entire Rover.
>> And you're the driver,
correct?
>> I am one of the drivers, yes.
>> Okay.
>> We have a whole team.
We build command sequences
ahead of time that tell it
everything we want to do
for the day.
And then it goes about
its business all by itself.
And when it's done, it says,
"Okay, here's what happened."
>> This thing doesn't just
roll around all day.
In fact, as we speak,
it's searching for evidence
of ancient life
and water on Mars.
It can actually analyze gases
and organics all by itself
and then send that data
back to Earth.
Just an amazing feat
of engineering.
Oh, and listen to this,
it also takes selfies.
[camera shutter clicking]
Is there technology here
filtering down to automobiles?
>> There are image processing
algorithms and things
that are on here to look
for hazards and things like that
that can be adapted and used.
We actually had one of our
colleagues work on
the self-driving car.
>> Can we drive this one?
Is that possible?
>> Um, the problem with driving
this one is you have to build
the command sequences
the same way we do for
the Rover on Mars.
>> Right.
>> So we have a stripped down
model over here.
>> Oh, the stripped one,
the base model.
>> Exactly.
So this is the Scarecrow.
This is our mobility mock-up.
I wanna introduce you to Gareth.
>> Hey.
>> He's gonna show you
how to drive it.
>> Gareth, how are you?
>> Jay. Good, how are you?
>> This is called Scarecrow,
you said?
>> This is called Scarecrow.
>> Why is this Scarecrow?
>> Because it doesn't
have a brain.
>> That's why they call me
Scarecrow at the network.
I had no idea.
>> Well I'm gonna leave you
in Gareth's capable hands.
>> Okay, well thank you,
thank you very much.
Thank you.
>> So let's start with
something simple.
The top button
in the middle, there, says
"forward five meters."
♪ ♪
This is really the workhorse
of our mobility testing
in the Mars Yard.
We do the vast majority
of our testing with this
especially before we do anything
with VSTB.
>> You know, for $2.5 billion,
I expect a little more
horsepower, maybe some
leather interior.
But that's okay.
Let's pick up the pace here.
This is a show about going fast.
Stop.
Wow.
>> So we're gonna aim to
put it over some rocks.
So here you're gonna see
the vehicle ascend
this rock that we've placed
in front of it.
So you'll notice that one thing
we try to do is when
one side of the vehicle
is going over a rock...
>> Right.
>> We don't want the whole
vehicle to stop rolling.
>> Right.
>> So we have a differential
on top of the vehicle
and that makes sure that
when one wheel goes up on
one side, the other goes down.
>> Okay, sure,
it's a little bit slow,
but incredibly efficient.
And keep in mind, the real Rover
is doing this right now,
more than 249,000,000 miles away
on Mars and in, believe me,
far worse conditions.
Well Gareth, thank you.
It's fascinating.
>> You're very welcome.
>> So what if NASA made
a production car?
Would you buy it?
Well, they're not quite
there yet, but they have
adapted the technology
from the Mars Rover and made
an Earth Rover car, called
the Modular Robotic Vehicle.
Pretty catchy, huh?
The MRV, for short,
is incredibly nimble
and designed with
urban driving in mind.
It's completely electronic,
allowing for remote control
and even full autonomy.
It has a top speed
of 43 miles an hour
and can hold a charge
for 62 miles.
But the coolest feature
adapted from the Rover
is its four independently
actuated wheels,
each with its own
steering system,
allowing them to rotate
180 degrees and sneak into some
pretty tight parking spaces.
However, you're probably
more likely to see this thing
on another planet,
where there's always
plenty of parking,
there's really not
that much trouble.
I had a heart problem.
I was told to begin my
Aspirin regimen,
and I just didn't listen.
Until I almost lost my life.
My doctors again ordered
me to take Aspirin,
and I do.
Be sure to talk to your doctor
before you begin an
Aspirin regimen.
Listen to the doctor.
Take it seriously.
How do you gauge the
greatness of an SUV?
Is it to carry cargo...
or to carry on a legacy?
Its show of strength...
or its sign of intelligence?
In crossing harsh terrain...
or breaking new ground?
This is the Mercedes-Benz
SUV family.
If you've never seen
yourself in a Mercedes,
you've never seen these offers.
Lease the GLA 250
for just $379 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz
Spring Event.
Hurry in before April 30th.
Mornings were made for
better things than
rheumatoid arthritis
or psoriatic arthritis.
When considering
another treatment,
ask about XELJANZ XR,
a once-daily pill for adults
with moderate to severe
rheumatoid arthritis or
active psoriatic arthritis
for whom methotrexate did
not work well enough.
It can reduce
pain, swelling,
and significantly improve
physical function.
XELJANZ XR can
lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened.
As have tears in the
stomach or intestines,
serious allergic reactions,
low blood cell counts,
higher liver tests and
cholesterol levels.
Don't start XELJANZ XR
if you have an infection.
Your doctor should
perform blood tests before
and while taking XELJANZ XR,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you've been
somewhere fungal infections
are common and if you have had
TB, hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Don't let another morning go by
without asking your doctor
about XELJANZ XR.
When did you see the sign?
Don't let another morning go by
withoWhen I needed tooctor
jumpstart sales.
Build attendance for an event.
Help people find their way.
FASTSIGNS designed new
directional signage.
...and got them back on track.
Get started at fastsigns.com.
At Hilton.com,
I can choose from all their
different hotel brands...
Like a DoubleTree
for my cousins.
A Homewood Suites
for my uncle.
A Hampton for
my sister and her kids.
And the Waldorf Astoria
Beverly Hills for me.
Can I get a..?
Thank you.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
Really?
[horn honks]
Man this is what I feel like
when I wear regular shoes,
cramped and uncomfortable.
We can arrange a little upgrade.
Which is why I wear Skechers...
Wide Fit shoes.
They have extra room throughout.
They're like a luxury
ride for my feet.
Try Skechers
Wide Fit shoes.
[big band music]
♪ ♪
>> Buckle up, folks.
It's time to Assess & Caress
with Donald Osborne.
♪ ♪
>> ♪ If you love classic cars ♪
♪ Then Donald loves you ♪
♪ ♪
[cash register bell rings]
[bell dings]
>> Well we are back once again
with our automotive historian
and appraiser, Donald Osborne.
Donald, thank you, again.
Tell us what these three cars
have in common.
>> Well, today we're celebrating
the Space Age.
And these are three examples
of the Space Age in their
time period.
We've got the 1937
Panhard Dynamic.
A 1961 Chrysler 300G.
And a 1972 Citroen SM.
>> Well let's start
with the Dynamic.
>> This car is pure Buck Rogers
space futurism.
This car was designed by Panhard
to be as advanced
as it possibly could be.
Using all the lessons
of aerodynamics seen on
the earlier Chrysler Airflow,
you see the waterfall grill
and the fenders that are
integrated into the body
to manage the airflow.
The covered wheels.
And they also wanted to
make sure that this car,
in terms of being advanced
as a driving experience,
they eliminated the A pillar.
So they put this
piece of glass here.
So you have almost total vision.
>> Oh, I see. There you are.
>> Isn't that astonishing?
>> Yeah, fantastic.
>> Hello, Jay!
>> [with French accent] Allo.
>> Let's go over
to the Chrysler.
>> Okay.
>> Many people talk about
what the first muscle cars were,
and you can make
a great argument for
the Chrysler letter cars
because they broke
the performance barrier
that had been held for decades
by the great Duesenberg SJ.
>> They were really fast.
This has a 413 engine, with two
four-barrel carburetors.
and it makes 375 horsepower,
which was a lot of horsepower
in 1961.
>> A big, heavy car, but fast.
>> Yeah. And this is a car,
when it came out, they used to
think they were sort of ugly.
They were so far-out looking,
in terms of Space Age styling.
I mean, they really looked like
rockets coming out the back.
And now they're just so
classically American.
>> Now let's go to one of my
absolutely favorite cars
on the entire planet,
the Citroen SM.
The Citroen SM is a marriage of
this wonderful French bodywork
engineering chassis,
and a Maserati V6 engine.
>> You know, the one thing
about Citroen, they always
look like the future,
because it doesn't look
like any other car.
It looks like something
that would come around
the turn of the next century.
Let's show people what it's like
under the hood.
This is what really intimidated
American mechanics
back in the day.
What you have here are
these spheres, which are
just brilliant.
They're filled with
fluid on one side
and there's nitrogen
on the other.
And it's a thick rubber.
And when the compressor works,
the rubber pushes the fluid,
and it raises the car
up and down.
I mean, it's a brilliant system.
There's no springs, it's quiet.
It does look intimidating,
but it's really not.
It's just a different way
of doing things.
All right, so we have
three choices here.
Which one of these
will appreciate the most
in the next five years?
Hmm. Let's see what The Donald
has to say.
This and more,
after a brief message
from our sponsors.
>> male announcer: Right from
GM's styling section,
in all its gleaming elegance,
is Le Sabre.
Her look of beauty begins
at her very nose,
that by day conceals
her close-set headlights,
to the cone of the stop light,
that glows like the afterburner
of a soaring jet.
She somehow seems already headed
for the sunlit foothills
of far-off places.
Yes, young in heart, Le Sabre.
For she was styled
with young ideas.
Things to come from
the production lines
of General Motors family
of fine auto--
[tape audio warbling]
[engine revs]
>> For more cool cars,
go to jaylenosgarage.cnbc.com.
♪ I'm tasting olives... ♪
♪ Roasted pine nuts... ♪
♪ Mmm this red pepper... ♪
♪ That's spicy stuff... ♪
Fresh flavor. Feel good food.
Sabra Hummus.
♪ I just had Sabra Hummus and
now I feel good! ♪
After walking six miles at
an amusement park...
Bill's back needed a
vacation from his vacation.
So he stepped on the
Dr. Scholl's kiosk.
It recommends our best
Custom Fit Orthotic
to relieve foot, knee, or
lower back pain.
So you can move more.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to move.
Guys go through a lot to
deal with shave irritation.
So, we built the
New Gillette SkinGuard
with a specialized guard
designed to reduce it.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
Gillette.
SARAH'S LAST TUITION
PAYMENT, SENT OFF.
FEELING GOOD?
OH YEAH.
NOW I'M READY TO
FOCUS ON MY PROJECT.
♪ ♪ ♪
THIS IS WHY WE PLAN.
YOU NEVER CEASE
TO AMAZE ME, MAYA.
SEE HOW INVESTING WITH A J.P.
MORGAN ADVISOR CAN HELP YOU.
VISIT YOUR LOCAL CHASE BRANCH.
You.
You inspired us to
create Internet
that puts you in charge.
That handles anything.
That protects what's important.
And reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
Simple, Easy, Awesome.
>> And we're back
with Donald Osborne.
[bell dings]
All right, Donald,
which of these vehicles
has appreciated the most?
>> First of all,
starting with the Dynamic,
a car like this sold a few years
ago for about $76,000.
And today you can probably
get one for about $78,000.
[bell dings]
So a bit of appreciation
because they are
interesting objects.
>> Right.
>> The Chrysler,
about five years ago,
one of these would cost
about $95,000.
Today, it would be
about $92,000.
It suffered a bit from
the general softening
of the market for big,
1950s American cars.
>> But if you're buying cars
by the pound,
that's still the best deal.
>> Absolutely.
Five years ago, a really nice
Citroen SM might have
cost you $40,000.
Today, a good one will cost
$75,000.
[bell dings]
>> It is the Citroen.
[imitating French laugh]
[victorious organ music]
♪ ♪
>> The best of France and Italy.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
>> I'm real excited,
'cause one of my favorite
customizers is coming
by the garage today.
His name is Gene Winfield.
Legendary hot rodder,
custom car builder.
Oh, by the way,
Gene is 89 years old.
How cool is that?
He's bringing one of
my favorite cars.
It's called the Reactor.
Now I've never seen
this car in person,
but when I was a kid,
I had pictures of it on my wall.
Here he comes now.
Hey, Gene, how you doing?
>> Great, Jay.
How you been?
>> It looks fantastic.
>> Thank you.
>> Explain to people
what we have here.
>> This is a turbocharge
Corvair.
>> Right.
>> Front-wheel drive.
>> On a Citroen chassis.
>> Tell me where your
styling ideas come from.
Did it come from NASA?
Just out of your head?
>> No, well partly out of
my head, and then I got ahold
of a designer, Ben Delphia.
>> Right.
>> So he did the final
design for me.
>> And, of course,
the engineering is
really amazing.
Nobody was doing
a front-wheel drive hot rod.
This is about the only one
at the time, isn't it?
>> For sure, the only one.
>> Can we open the hood?
>> Yeah, sure.
>> Oh, look at that.
Well, and I see all the Citroen.
You even have a Corvair
generator from the period.
>> Yes, I made the adapter
myself to couple up the Corvair
engine to the Citroen transaxle.
>> Tell me about the--the--
well it's not
a steering wheel, is it?
Steering--
>> No, it's a steering
apparatus.
>> Yeah.
>> It's called a twist-wrist
steering.
>> Right.
>> See, so you actually turn it
and you can turn these handles.
>> Oh, I got you.
>> Like that.
>> And that's the original
color, did you ever change
the color?
>> No, I repainted a couple
of times throughout the years,
but it's always been
a green metal flake.
>> Yeah, I remember there's
a picture of Shatner
leaning up against this.
>> That's right.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Can we take it out
for a ride?
>> Yeah, sure.
>> Well that'd be cool.
>> Sure, you bet.
>> Let's do it.
[engine turns over]
Put that top down.
Let's peel out of here.
>> All right.
Here we go.
[engine roaring]
[surf rock music]
♪ ♪
>> The Reactor looks like
it should go about
1,000 miles an hour.
Kinda like Gene himself.
This guy never slows down.
♪ ♪
What's the most fun part?
Designing it? Building it?
Driving it?
>> Building it, building it.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Yeah, building it was
the most fun part.
>> People don't realize
how many man hours go into
something like this, huh?
What are you looking at here?
About 3,000 man hours?
Something like that?
>> Yeah.
[engine rumbles]
>> You know, sometimes,
looking cool isn't always
practical.
[coughs]
Or healthy.
♪ ♪
>> Whoo. [laughs]
>> A little smoky inside.
>> You--you're a good sport.
>> No, no.
You know, if you had told me
50 years ago I'd get
asphyxiated with Gene Winfield
in the car I dreamed about
when I was 15 years old,
it's pretty amazing.
>> Well, thank you.
>> Yeah, but it really is.
Doesn't get any cooler
than that.
So why is space so important
to the automobile?
>> Hold on. This is major.
This is deep.
>> Well, it revolutionized
styling...
This looks like the thrusters
from a jet, coming out the back.
Modernized technology...
>> Now you've got a mean,
fighting machine.
>> And helped influence
some of the most expensive
and advanced machinery
in the world.
[w