Depends on who you ask.
- If I tell you this is fun,
I don't know what
you're gonna put me on next.
- The power of nostalgia
is real.
Bring back some memories when
you step on that accelerator?
- Oh, that's lovely.
- But one thing's for sure.
The better the technology,
the safer we all are.
[groans]
- You okay, Jay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
At least that's what
I keep telling my wife.
Honey, we can get to your
mom's house much quicker.
As for me,
I can't wait to see
what the next
next generation has in store.
Remember, you're never too old
to fall down.
>> On your mark, get set, go.
Tonight on "Jay
Leno's Garage"...
Fun with your mom's car.
Water and cars.
>> All right, let's do it.
Water can power cars...
>> We're generating steam
right now.
>> But it can also destroy them.
So when oil and water mix,
is it always trouble?
I'm sliding around.
To find out, Jeff Dunham and I
take to the high seas for the
rematch of the century.
>> Are you kidding me?
They're both morons.
>> [laughing]
Comedian Alonzo Bodden and I
get our beer goggles on...
>> Jay Leno,
>> And it ain't pretty.
This is about as dangerous
as it gets.
We'll go back to the age
of steam.
There's a fire.
Look, I'll drive.
>> Let's go.
>> The glory days
of firefighting.
We'll be there in about
20 minutes.
And I'll drive this huge,
amphibious monster...
>> All right, Jay, you're
officially feet-wet
in a U.S. Navy LCAC.
>> U.S. Navy's massive,
$40 million hovercraft.
>> Whoa, we're coming
around quick.
>> Mayday, Mayday.
Abort mission.
I think I've killed
everybody on board.
Because tonight it's all about
going fast, being loud,
and mixing oil and water.
And the nice thing is,
there's no traffic.
So put on your Speedo,
'cause I can guarantee
we're gonna get wet.
Let's do this.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
You know, there's an old saying
that oil and water don't mix,
but in a lot of ways, they do.
In this episode, you'll see
vehicles that have some
connection with water:
amphibious vehicles,
steam-powered cars,
or even a vehicle like this
that was styled to look like
a boat.
the 1916 Crane-Simplex.
This was meant to mimic some
of the great cigarette boats
of the teens.
They were fast.
They were agile.
They were sexy.
You enter it like a boat.
You get in from the middle.
This is all mahogany.
All sorts of ship-like cues
throughout the whole thing.
And this was not an inexpensive
car back in the day.
In 1916, this car cost $33,000.
And when you figure the average
home was around $1,200...
that's a lot of money.
Although this was not especially
fast car, it was a very
powerful car, much like these
locomotives right out
the window here.
[train engine toots]
Thank you.
Boy, right on cue.
Right now, we're gonna settle a
score with Jeff Dunham.
>> Let's do this.
>> [laughing]
>> Last season,
we raced 1960s Amphicars.
>> Come on,
you can beat this moron.
>> Through treachery and deceit,
I lost.
>> Yee-haw!
>> So we're heading out to
Castaic Lake, where we'll have
our long-awaited rematch.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Jeff Dunham, a year ago,
you and I raced
on this very lake,
and I lost.
But I'm back
to settle the score.
>> Jay Leno: all chin,
no action.
>> Let's see if you can do it
again, puppet boy.
>> At least I can do voices.
>> This time we're
racing WaterCars.
Ten times--
>> You sure you wanna--
>> What's that?
[laughing]
All right, enough of that.
Let's check out the WaterCars.
[energetic music]
♪ ♪
I'm seeing these for the first
time, just like you are.
These are called WaterCars.
They're brand-new.
Whereas the Amphicar was sort of
slow and helped revolutionize
drowning, this you can drive
like a car.
It looks like a Jeep, but you
can take it in the water.
They've got about
300 horsepower.
The Amphicar had, what--
>> Two?
>> 52 horsepower,
something like that?
>> I don't know.
>> Let's meet Fred Selby.
Fred, come on in.
Fred is the--one of the
partners, one of the founding
partners of this deal.
>> Hey, Jay.
>> Explain to him what we have.
>> Yeah, well, these
are WaterCars.
They're the fastest amphibious
vehicles in the world.
They'll do 45 mile an hour
in the water.
>> Really?
Pull a skier?
>> Yeah, it does.
>> Good Lord.
>> We make 'em here
in Southern California.
Sold about 50,
and we deliver 'em
around the world.
We actually build these
from scratch.
It's a fiberglass hull
that we build ourselves.
We put a chromoly chassis inside
it and embed it all in the
fiberglass, then kind of wrap it
with closed-cell foam
for flotation.
And our own pump that pushes
it--it's like a big Jet Ski when
you're in the water.
>> And do you steer it with the
steering wheel?
>> When you enter into the
water, you do everything just as
you're operating a car.
>> Well, you enter the water in
a car, you've probably
been drinking.
That's the trouble, though.
>> [laughing] Yeah.
It's not hard to enter
the water...
>> Yeah.
>> In a car.
It's hard to exit.
>> Right, right.
>> But we can do that here.
>> So what does it look like
when it's in boat mode?
>> Let me show you.
>> Okay. It has a sail.
[whirring]
Oh, that's impressive.
>> Oh, you're like a kid at
a candy store.
[moaning]
>> Well, I do have new twin
boys, and they would fit right
in the back.
>> It's for the kids--
that's what.
You're not thinking of yourself.
>> Never.
>> What a wonderful father.
>> I am.
Where's the water line?
>> When you're in the water, you
can open the doors.
>> You can open the doors?
>> Yeah, it's--
>> And it won't sink?
>> We've been at this 16 years.
16 year--we've never sunk one.
>> Well, let's open the hood.
Let's see what the engine
looks like, yeah.
>> Let's take a look.
It's fairly
clean installation.
There's a Honda 3.7,
single exhaust system on it.
>> An Amphicar's
a freshwater vehicle.
Can you take this in seawater?
>> Yeah, absolutely.
>> Really?
>> Our test bed is saltwater.
Okay, guys.
>> Pretty cool.
Hey, Jeff, you ready to do it?
Let's take these for a ride.
>> A race.
>> A race. Let's go for a race.
>> A race, race. Let's go.
>> Wait, wait, wait--we got to
do a little training on it.
>> Come on, Jeff, we're
Amphi people.
>> No, no, hey, come on, guys.
>> How hard can it be?
>> It's four gears.
>> No, you need to know
how to drive.
>> I know how to drive.
>> Jay, Jay, come on.
>> Fred, don't worry about us.
We'll be right.
[engines turn over]
>> Guys...
♪ ♪
>> So this is gonna be
just like last time.
>> Yeah, except it'll be fair
this time.
>> It was fair.
>> The race will start when we
hit the first buoy.
And it's two miles to the
finish line.
>> May the best water
driver win.
>> [laughs]
Leno and Dunham both
begged me to be in this.
Are you kidding me?
Cars were made to be on land.
Boats were made to be on water.
That's it.
>> Are my wheels up?
>> Yeah.
>> These guys are dumbasses.
Dumbasses, dumb...ass...es.
>> Pretty amazing vehicle.
Just feels like a car
that's floating on the water.
It's hilarious.
>> Is this exciting?
I don't think so.
Do you see anybody on
the shore cheering?
I don't think so.
It's a desolate place.
No one cares.
>> Okay, line 'em up.
I'm waiting for Jeff now.
Jeff, you ready?
>> I'm ready.
>> Did you notice, Leno is not
wearing a life vest because if
he falls in the water,
his chin will keep him afloat.
[laughing]
See how I did that?
It's like a joke.
Shut up.
>> All right, on your mark,
get set, go.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
When that front end goes up,
you can't see anything.
>> Gonna get you, Leno!
♪ ♪
>> [laughing]
Yee-haw.
I don't think these two machines
could be more closely matched.
Right now it's just
driver's skill.
[laughing]
All right, this is stupid fun.
♪ ♪
45 miles an hour on the water
is a lot faster than it is
in a car.
I'll tell you that.
It's pounding here.
>> [laughs]
>> Dunham is losing this.
There's no doubt about that.
I guess he should've
let me drive.
I weigh less.
>> When Dunham doesn't have
that puppet to help him,
he's hopeless.
♪ ♪
Dunham trying to cut me off.
>> [chuckling]
>> I think we got him.
I think we got him.
♪ ♪
By a nose.
Yes!
Very, very close.
The score has been settled.
You know, I don't know whether
it was the sea spray, but I
thought I saw a tear in Jeff's
eye when I beat him.
Thank you.
>> There is going to be no
living with Mr. Dunham.
I think I'm gonna find
something to do tonight.
He's not a good loser.
[engines roaring]
>> [laughing]
>> What a sore loser.
There you have it, folks.
I evened the score.
What we need now
but that'll just have to wait
till next season.
>> Are we done?
Did they finish their cute
little boat race?
It's time for me to go home.
Hello, anyone?
Nothing.
[wind rustling]
>> Coming up...
>> This craft's filled up to
about 36,000 pounds of fuel,
and it'll last probably
about five hours.
>> Wow.
How much horsepower does it take
to drive one of these?
>> A lot.
Here's a hint: the LCAC
makes the Hellcat
look like a Volkswagen Bug.
SARAH'S LAST TUITION
PAYMENT, SENT OFF.
FEELING GOOD?
OH YEAH.
NOW I'M READY TO
FOCUS ON MY PROJECT.
♪ ♪ ♪
THIS IS WHY WE PLAN.
YOU NEVER CEASE
TO AMAZE ME, MAYA.
SEE HOW INVESTING WITH A J.P.
MORGAN ADVISOR CAN HELP YOU.
VISIT YOUR LOCAL CHASE BRANCH.
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
Experience the style,
craftsmanship and technology
that have made the RX
the leading luxury
SUV of all time.
Lease the 2019 RX 350 for
$409 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
We're Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh and
you may remember us from...
Your very first sandwich,
Your move-in-day...feast.
Your bold canine caper.
[child] That's not for you,
Bandit!
Your dinner in the dark.
Your mammoth masterpiece.
[whispering] Your 3:47 AM snack.
And...whatever happened here...
Because we make Deli Fresh
with all the good of the deli,
no artificial preservatives and
no added nitrates or nitrites.
Make every sandwich count
with Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh.
>> Not all amphibious vehicles
are for fun and games.
Some of them serve a
much-needed purpose.
We're off to Camp Pendleton,
where we'll board an LCAC,
a land-to-water hovercraft
that's built to save lives.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
On D-Day, thousands of U.S. Navy
landing crafts transported
equipment and infantry to the
beaches of Normandy.
But once they hit land,
they were exposed
and vulnerable.
The invention and evolution of
the hovercraft eventually gave
birth to U.S. Navy LCAC,
allowing for more efficient
water-to-land maneuvering, and
more importantly, reduction
in casualties.
Captain Amidon,
how are you, sir?
>> Good morning, welcome to
Assault Craft Unit 5,
home of The Swift Intruders.
>> Well, I'm very excited.
Yeah, thank you.
This should be a lot of fun.
>> Are you ready to get started?
>> Let's do it.
>> All right.
>> So let's get you changed.
>> Okay. Ta-da.
>> Very nice.
>> We got boots
for you, socks...
>> Oh, great.
>> A T-shirt, the whole thing.
>> Cool, cool.
So what do the initials LCAC
stand for, exactly?
>> LCAC stands for Landing Craft
Air Cushion, so they actually
ride on a small cushion of air.
>> This monster is 87 feet long,
weighs 182 tons, and can go up
to 70 knots.
Basically, if you see
this thing coming at you,
get out of the way.
And lucky me, I get to drive
this thing.
>> First, we need to get you
trained up.
So we're ready to go through
our simulator.
>> And you put quarters in this,
or is it just straight ahead?
Am I right here?
>> Yes, sir.
>> You're right there
in that seat.
>> Okay.
Usually, each LCAC pilot
must do 196 hours of training.
Guys, we're spinning.
>> Oh, no, we're coming
around quick.
>> Okay, I think I've killed
everybody on board.
Hang on.
But as a former talk show host,
20 minutes should do the trick.
Mayday, mayday, abort mission.
>> [laughing]
>> Well, let me ask
you something.
Now, it goes 55 miles an hour.
And during R&R, any guys ever
try to waterski behind these?
>> You know, Jay, I've never
seen 'em do it, but I don't
think they'd make it very long
back there behind the prop.
>> How bad is the wind blast
behind it?
>> So it'd be a
Hurricane Katrina...
>> Really?
>> Worse.
>> So the waterskiing thing
is out.
>> It's out.
>> Okay.
>> So here at ACU 5, we're a lot
like you, you know?
We're a self-maintained garage.
You know, a lot of people, when
they have a boat breaks down,
they take it to a shipyard
or to a boat shop.
We do everything in house.
>> I know the guys want--just
want to know, what kind of
horsepower are we talking
about here?
>> A lot.
We're looking 5,000 horsepower.
>> Per engine.
>> Per engine?
>> And how many engines
on the vehicle?
>> We have four.
>> Four--so we're looking at
20,000 horsepower.
Okay, now we're talking.
Let's do this.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
Well, take me through it
now, okay?
These are your two primary
engines to move it forward.
But there are other engines in
here, correct?
>> That's correct, sir.
>> Okay.
>> So if you go back here after
the craft, there's two turbofan
engines per side.
>> Okay, and those spin fans
which force the air to
lift it up?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Okay, okay.
The layout is pretty basic.
The engines in the back make it
go, and the engines on the side
make it hover.
Now, can you move one of these
when those engines
aren't running?
>> Uh...
>> I mean, can you even tow it?
There aren't, like, any wheels
for when it's down...
>> No, sir.
>> That can roll, of any kind.
So it's to to be running--
it's got to be running to move.
>> Right, on its own power.
>> You're not gonna jump-start.
You're not gonna get a bunch of
guys--"let's push this baby.
Get a--jump-start it."
>> Pop the clutch.
>> Not gonna happen, no.
No popping the clutch on this.
Okay.
And what is your miles per
gallon, would you say?
>> [laughing]
>> Or is it gallons per mile?
>> It's gallons per hour, right?
>> Gallons per hour.
>> It's gallons per hour.
This craft is filled up to about
36,000 pounds of fuel.
It'll last probably about
five hours.
>> Wow, okay.
My dad had a Cadillac like that.
Wow.
Is this goal of this to bring
vehicles off-ship into land--
a tank or whatever it might be?
>> It was designed for
high-speed, ship-to-shore
maneuver--to get Marine Corps
equipment ashore as quickly
as possible.
>> If you had this,
you would've used this
at Normandy Beach,
in other words.
>> Absolutely.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> It's the latest generation
of craft for assaulting
the beach.
>> Just filled with soldiers,
and you can come in, okay.
All right,
I've had enough training.
I think it's time
we went for a ride.
>> Clear to come up
on cushion for seat.
Feet wet when ready.
The ship is eight nautical
miles now.
>> Roger.
>> It'll take about 13 minutes
to get there.
>> Our mission objective:
hover fast for three miles
and then dock with
the USS "Comstock."
Piece of cake!
I've had 20 minutes of training.
Let's do this.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
>> Jay, this is what's called
"on cushion."
We're off of the landing rails,
and we're actually floating
on a cushion of air.
>> That's our ship out there
on the left?
>> That's correct, Jay.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
All right, Jay, and this is
what's called transitioning
from feet dry to feet wet.
Feet dry over land,
feet wet when we get out to sea.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
All right, Jay,
you're officially feet wet
in a U.S. Navy LCAC.
>> Very cool.
[epic music]
♪ ♪
It's really much smoother than
I thought it would be.
It's much smoother than a boat
would be under
the same circumstances.
And it's moving along.
What are you, about 45 knots?
>> We're at 30 right now, Jay.
>> 30 knots, okay.
Ever spot whales out here?
>> We do.
>> Yeah?
>> Quite frequently.
♪ ♪
All right, Jay, what we did
right now is, we came all stop.
So I'm gonna get you up
in the seat.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Sorry.
>> Tricky up there.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Okay, this is a lot trickier
than it looks.
Maybe I needed 22 minutes
of training.
>> It's tricky up there.
>> This is--
>> Use your right leg first.
>> It's the helmet that makes
it the trickiest.
Let me see if I can do this.
Here we go.
And after some awkward
maneuvering,
I get to take the helm.
And believe me,
this ain't no simulator.
I feel like I'm in one of those
bad movies where the admiral's
son is given command, and they
take it away from the guy who
actually knows what he's doing.
[laughter]
>> Seven nautical miles
to the ship right now.
>> Go forward?
>> Yeah, push 'em
all the way forward.
>> All the way forward.
Can't feel any power.
Am I moving?
>> Yup, we are.
>> I want to go a little bit
right, right?
♪ ♪
Now, just to be clear,
I'm only steering this thing.
The real professionals are doing
the work of operating the
navigation and the acceleration.
But in true
show business tradition,
I'll take all the credit.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
>> As we get a little farther
out to sea, you'll feel
the waves pick up a little bit.
>> Yeah.
>> Pretty heavy seas.
♪ ♪
I've driven monster trucks,
fire trucks, even tanks,
but that's child's play
compared to trying to pilot
this incredible machine.
♪ ♪
And believe me, folks,
this is a lot harder
than it looks.
♪ ♪
>> Congratulations on your first
well deck.
>> Hey, that was great,
you guys.
Very cool.
Okay, so the Navy wasn't
entirely comfortable
with me docking a
$40 million hovercraft.
>> We're gonna shut down
the main engines...
>> Right.
>> And then we'll get you off
the boat.
>> Cool.
>> Maybe next time.
♪ ♪
>> Jay's on deck!
>> Welcome aboard, Jay,
to the USS "Comstock."
>> Thank you, sir.
>> There you go.
I got a fine, little hat
for you.
>> Oh, cool.
>> That's yours.
So you gotta wear it with pride.
Oh, it fits perfect.
>> There you go.
>> Okay, so we're assembled on
the flight deck.
>> Cool.
When I was a kid, I always
enjoyed seeing Bob Hope standing
on the ship with the golf club,
saying hello to
the men and women.
And now I get to do it too.
It's a real honor.
>> I!
>> all: Am a United States
sailor.
I will support and defend
the constitution
of the United States
of America and I will obey
the orders of those appointed
over me.
I represent the fighting spirit
of the Navy and those who have
gone before me to defend freedom
and democracy around the world.
I proudly serve my country's
Navy Combat Team with honor,
courage, and commitment.
I am committed to excellence
and the fair treatment of all.
>> Booya!
Hey, bring it in, please.
Bring it in.
Hey, it's a beautiful day
onboard USS "Comstock."
And we have the privilege of
having a special guest onboard.
We all know him as the host
of "The Tonight Show"
and of "Jay Leno's Garage."
It's my privilege and honor
to introduce to you Jay Leno.
>> Thank you.
Well, thank you, guys.
Are we on?
There we go.
There we go, cool.
This was really an honor,
you guys.
Thank you.
It's really exciting to do.
And we just want to show people
what you guys do
and how well you do it.
And they let me drive it today.
I see why they won't let me
drive it again.
[laughter]
But anyway, I just want to say
what an honor it is.
And I'd like to be able to shake
each and every one of you's hand
if I could.
I would like that privilege
so much.
So thank you.
I'll give it back
to the Captain.
>> All right, thanks, guys.
Appreciate it.
>> Thank you.
Thanks, guys.
>> How's it going?
>> Thank you.
Thank you, gentlemen.
>> Can I get a--
>> Thank you, sir.
>> Did I get you?
I missed you.
>> You got me twice.
>> Oh, I got you twice. Okay.
>> Did him twice already.
>> One, two...
>> Say cheese.
>> Thanks, everybody.
>> Carry on, please.
[applause]
>> Coming up...
Ow! I'm getting covered
with hot sparks.
Find out where the term
"fighting fire with fire"
really comes from.
You know, I see why a lot
of houses burned down.
After walking six miles at
an amusement park...
Bill's back needed a
vacation from his vacation.
So he stepped on the
Dr. Scholl's kiosk.
It recommends our best
Custom Fit Orthotic
to relieve foot, knee, or
lower back pain.
So you can move more.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to move.
I had no symptoms
of Hepatitis C.
Mine...
...caused liver damage.
EPCLUSA treats all main types
of chronic Hep C.
Whatever your type,
ask your doctor
if EPCLUSA is your kind of cure.
I had the common type.
Mine was rare.
EPCLUSA has a 98%
overall cure rate.
I just found out
about my hepatitis C.
I knew for years.
EPCLUSA is only one
pill, once a day,
taken with or without
food for 12 weeks.
Before starting EPCLUSA,
your doctor will
test if you have had
hepatitis B, which may flare up
and could cause
serious liver problems
during and after treatment.
Tell your doctor if you
have had hepatitis B
other liver or
kidney problems, HIV
or other medical conditions...
...and all medicines you take,
including herbal supplements.
Taking amiodarone
with EPCLUSA may
cause a serious slowing
of your heart rate.
Common side effects include
headache and tiredness
Ask your doctor today, if
EPCLUSA is your kind of cure.
♪Work so hard give it everything
you got♪
♪Strength of a lioness tough as
a knot♪
♪Rocking the stage and we're
never gonna stop♪
♪All Strength, No Sweat... just
in case you forgot♪
♪All Strength, No Sweat...♪
♪No No No Sweat...♪♪
Hey Mercedes,
how about letting
your hair down a little?
How about a car for
people who don't play golf?
Hey Mercedes!
Mix it up a little.
How about something for a guy
who doesn't want
a corner office?
Hey Mercedes, I
don't even own a tie.
Do you think I need
a mahogany dashboard?
Hey Mercedes, can you make
it a little cooler in here?
[ A-Class ]
I am setting the temperature
to 68 degrees.
We hear you.
We made a car that does, too.
The all-new A-Class.
All-new thinking
starting at $32,500.
At the Mercedes-Benz
Spring Event.
Going on now.
When I book at Hilton.com
I get to select my room
from the floor plan...
Free Wi-Fi...
...and the Price
Match Guarantee.
So with Hilton
there is no catch.
Yeah the only catch
is I'm never leaving.
No I'm serious,
I live here now.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
I had a heart problem.
I was told to begin my
Aspirin regimen,
Book at Hilton.com
and I just didn't listen.
Until I almost lost my life.
My doctors again ordered
me to take Aspirin,
and I do.
Be sure to talk to your doctor
before you begin an
Aspirin regimen.
Listen to the doctor.
Take it seriously.
♪ ♪
>> My name is Sabrina Siek,
and I'm the lead researcher at
"Ripley's Believe It or Not!"
They were here in beautiful
Port Canaveral
where the launches go off,
the cruises go out,
and you can go see a great view
at the Exploration Tower.
Behind me is another great view:
Livio De Marchi's wooden
Ferrari F50.
The wooden Ferrari was created
by Italian artist
Livio De Marchi,
who's from Venice, Italy
and he started to create them
for the Carnival of Venice.
He would actually take them
on the canals of Venice
and make one every single year.
He wanted to start making these
cars, because he was bullied by
some of other boats.
He was in a wooden paddleboat,
and he really needed
to stand out.
So, I mean, what better way than
having a Ferrari F50 going down
the canals?
>> De Marchi is like a real,
live Geppetto, using only hand
tools to make his work truly
come to life.
>> So this car is the exact same
dimensions of the Ferrari F50.
In terms of weight, it's about
2,200 pounds, and the Ferrari
F50 weighs 2,800 pounds.
All the other details are almost
spot-on, from the wheels to the
air vents to the zippers behind
the headrests, where the targa
top would come off.
>> A real Ferrari F50
goes over 200 miles an hour.
This, not so much.
>> [laughing]
>> But that's okay,
because you look cool
driving it.
>> Bon voyage.
[laughing]
[acoustic strumming]
♪ ♪
>> Okay, we've seen vehicles
that travel on water.
How about vehicles that
pump water?
Firefighting was pretty much
the same from the 1840s
of the 20th century.
You had a horse-drawn wagon
using massive horsepower
to pull a steamer
to pump the water.
The part that changed
dramatically
was how you got to the fire.
The horse-drawn carriage did
improve response time,
but by 1905,
the idea of motorized
fire engines started
gaining popularity.
And in 1922,
the New York Fire Department
finally retired their
last horse-drawn engine.
[bell dinging]
[horses panting]
Hey, Andy, how are you?
>> Lovely.
>> Come on down.
One-time fireman and longtime
friend Andy Swift has been
restoring antique fire engines
for years, and he's one of the
best, if not the best,
in the country.
He works with everyone, from
private collectors to museums,
and that's why I brought him
out here.
>> Tell folks what we have here.
>> What we got here is a 1914
Front Drive Christie tractor.
>> Now, J. Walter Christie is
kind of a hero of mine.
He was not the first one to come
up with a front-wheel drive
vehicle, but one of
the very first.
And his engineering is
really revolutionary.
Since fire departments had
so much of their equipment
wrapped up in horse-drawn
things,
what he did was
he enabled them to use
their old horse-drawn
steam engines
and hook them up to--
instead of horses,
a front-wheel drive tractor.
How much more economical
was this versus a horse?
'Cause imagine, a horse you had
to feed; you had veterinary
bills and all that
kind of thing.
>> The fire department saved 90
cents on a dollar...
>> Really?
>> When the horses left the
fire service.
>> Okay.
>> A lot of people say that was
a bad time because, you know,
the romance of firefighting
went out the window
when the horses left.
>> Yeah, but they still put
the fire out.
[laughing]
'Cause the horses took
a little longer to get there,
didn't they?
This could go 40 miles an hour.
>> Exactly.
Gas-burner versus hay-burner.
>> Right, right.
And this is where the expression
of fighting fire with fire
comes from, doesn't it?
Because you have to light
a fire in this,
and sparks come out the top,
so you can actually
set a fire
on your way to a fire,
couldn't you?
>> That's right.
>> So how much maintenance
was involved in this every day?
>> You're gonna clean your flus.
>> Right.
>> You know, wire brush 'em,
make sure that you--you get--
>> You smell smoke?
Look over that ridge.
>> Whoa.
>> Looks like there's
something on fire.
There's a fire.
Look, I'll drive.
>> Oh, nice.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Let's go.
>> All right, so much
for bad acting.
Let's go put out a fire.
[people screaming]
♪ ♪
[bell jangling]
>> Hose.
>> My end down?
>> Yup.
♪ ♪
We're getting the suction on.
We need it on there nice
and tight.
>> Now water's coming out
of the pond, where...
>> Check our fire again.
And you think gas mileage is
bad, wooden mileage is terrible.
>> What we're doing is,
we're heating up the water
to make steam,
which runs the pump,
which will pull the water
out of the lake.
Andy, how we lookin'?
>> We're looking good, Jay.
We got plenty of water
in the glass.
We're generating steam
right now, as that fire's going
and then this throttle
delivers the steam
to the steam cylinders.
>> Right.
The pistons move up and down--
that pushes the water.
>> Exactly. And look at that,
with five pounds on the gauge.
>> You know, I see why a lot of
houses burned down...
>> Oh, come on.
>> In the 1800s.
>> This is a nice--
>> Look, the house is on fire.
We're standing here.
>> Yeah, but you're putting out
the fire.
>> The house is on fire!
>> Look how good you look while
you're doing it!
>> My house is on fire.
Ow! And I'm getting covered with
hot sparks.
My beautiful--
my only denim shirt,
and it's getting a hole in it.
Burn slower!
We'll be there in about
20 minutes!
We're building pressure!
We'll be there in a little bit!
Well, you get the idea.
After a quick 20 minutes or so,
we're ready to go.
>> We're showing 25 pounds of
steam, and it wants to take off.
>> The slowest firemen in the
world are ready to go
put this thing out.
Come on, let's get up there!
>> Let's go!
♪ ♪
>> There we go.
[popping]
>> That's a little air.
♪ ♪
>> All right,
let's advance that hose.
>> You kind of get the idea
how this works.
We want to thank
the Burbank Fire Department
for putting up with
all this nonsense.
But you got to see
how they fought fires
over 100 years ago.
The equipment wasn't as good,
but the men are just as brave.
So, guys, thank you very much.
Thanks for being a part of it.
I don't think we're gonna be on
the calendar this year.
>> Ha!
♪ ♪
>> Coming up next...
>> I'm a close, personal
friend of Jay Leno.
>> Comedian Alonzo Bodden
drinks and drives...
Okay, ran over a cone...
Without drinking.
>> I'm not sure where you went.
I'm Ken Jacobus and I switched
to the Spark Cash Card
from Capital One.
I earn unlimited 2% cash back on
everything I buy.
And last year, I earned $36,000
in cash back.
Which I used to offer health
insurance to my employees.
What's in your wallet?
I had a heart problem.
I was told to begin my
Aspirin regimen,
and I just didn't listen.
Until I almost lost my life.
My doctors again ordered
me to take Aspirin,
and I do.
Be sure to talk to your doctor
before you begin an
Aspirin regimen.
Listen to the doctor.
Take it seriously.
When you book at Hilton.com,
you get the Price
Match Guarantee.
So if you find your
room at a lower rate,
Hilton is like...
We're gonna match that rate
and give you an extra 25% off.
What would travel sites do if
you found a different price?
That's not my problem,
it's your problem.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
Lobsterfest is on at Red Lobster
With the most lobster dishes
of the year
Like our classic
Lobster Lover's Dream...
So hurry in!
Lobsterfest ends
April twenty-first.
And now for a limited time,
get ten percent off
Red Lobster To Go.
Drivers just wont put their
phones down.
We need a solution.
Introducing... Smartdogs.
The first dogs trained to train
humans.
Stopping drivers from: Liking.
Selfie-ing.
And whatever this is.
Available to the public...
never.
Smartdogs are not the answer.
But GEICO has a simple tip.
Turn on "Do Not Disturb While
Driving" mode.
Brought to you by GEICO.
[electronic beeping]
♪ ♪
>> If you've never seen
"The Spy Who Loved Me,"
there's a villain trying to
take over the world,
Bond gets the girl,
and there's a cool car.
But not just any car,
a 1977 Lotus Esprit.
Oh, and it converts into a
submarine, because...
it's a Bond movie.
30 years later, Swiss automobile
manufacturer Rinspeed took
inspiration from James Bond
and made the sQuba: a one-off
concept car that literally turns
into a submarine.
Running on three electrical
motors, it can go over
70 miles an hour on land
and dive up to 35 feet in water.
However, for safety reasons,
there's no top.
That's right,
it's a convertible submarine,
which doesn't make
a lot of sense.
But you want to be sure
to bring a backup tuxedo.
And did I mention
it's fully autonomous?
Leaving Bond's hands free to--
[clears throat]
Do other things.
[jazzy music]
♪ ♪
Buckle up, folks.
It's time to Assess & Caress
with Donald Osborne.
>> ♪ If you love classic cars ♪
♪ Then Donald loves you ♪
♪ ♪
>> Once again, I'm Assess.
This is Caress.
And we are going to
discuss automobiles.
This is, of course,
Donald Osborne,
our appraiser extraordinaire.
He's brought three
vehicles today.
Decidedly a nautical theme.
Tell us what we have.
>> Well, Jay, we've got a 1944
Volkswagen Schwimmwagen.
This a 1966 Amphicar 770,
and a 1916 Crane-Simplex.
Let's start with
the Schwimmwagen.
>> Okay.
>> This is the amphibious
version of the VW Bug...
>> Right.
>> Which of course was developed
before World War II
as the Kraft durch Freude Wagen.
Like the U.S. Jeep, had a lot of
military applications on land
as the Kubelwagen.
And this, the Schwimmwagen, the
amphibious version of the car.
>> Is this something that was
just meant for swamps and
wetlands, or can you actually
cross a body of water in
this thing?
>> This is designed to go into
the water and totally swim.
>> Right.
>> You notice that it has
no doors.
>> Right.
>> The body is completely
sealed underneath.
The lights are mounted high.
The exhaust pipe and muffler is
mounted high.
>> Well, show me how they engage
the drive when you want to go in
the water.
>> Okay, so the way it's
explained to me, the person in
the backseat...
>> Schultzy.
>> Handling this--Schultzy.
>> "I see nothing!"
>> "I see nothing."
He hooks this up.
He then pushes down, and the
weight of the propeller connects
it with the driveshaft, and
you're off and running.
>> And is it the standard
Volkswagen engine,
4-cylinder?
>> The standard Volkswagen
4-cylinder engine.
>> Okay.
>> Exactly, as did the first
post-war VW.
For something completely
different, let's take a look at
the 1916 Crane-Simplex.
>> Well, I know a little
something about this one,
'cause it's my car.
Holbrook was the body-builder,
and Crane-Simplex was meant to
be an American Rolls-Royce.
The thing that makes this one
interesting was, they built
really big, boxy,
boring limousines.
So this is a one-off car
that was built specifically
just to display the,
"Look, we don't just build
boring limousines."
>> Exactly.
>> As you see, all sorts of bits
of brass and copper.
I mean, this is when an engine
looked like an engine.
>> Absolutely.
>> I mean, this carburetor looks
like a toilet bowl.
>> [laughing]
>> It's just a huge, enormous--
and really, it's--every time you
step on the gas, it's like
flushing seven gallons.
>> And it's also very emblematic
of the period when your
chauffeur had a lot of work to
do after he dropped you off
at home to keep all of this
cleaned and polished
and functioning...
>> Right.
>> Exactly the way it should.
Let's turn to the Amphicar.
>> I remember these when they
came out, 'cause it was such
a ridiculous concept.
But it actually works
quite well.
You can't help but smile when
you drive this thing.
>> The Amphicar is an
astonishing thing.
And, of course, the car, which
was made in only one series, was
called the Model 770.
And the 770 stood for seven
knots in the water, 70 miles per
hour on land...
>> Oh, okay.
>> Each equally scary.
Powered by a 4-cylinder
Triumph engine,
putting out close to
43 horsepower.
They ended up making somewhere
under 10,000 units for the
entire production run.
>> And in the United States, you
have to license it as both a car
and a boat.
>> Thereby doubling
your expenses...
>> Yeah.
>> Doubling your insurance.
So it really is for people who
have to have something by their
lake house that they could only
use there.
And the ones that survived
also were used very little.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Once the novelty wore off,
I think most of them were just
sort of parked in garages.
>> Okay, there we have our three
nautically-themed cars.
But investment-wise, which one
has the best potential?
If you bought one of these five
years ago, would you be
underwater, as Donald would say?
We'll find out.
>> I will reveal all.
>> This and more after a brief
message from our sponsors.
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
>> Here comes a dark cloud on
the horizon for anyone who runs
a toll bridge for a living:
the Amphicar, a new, imported
model, which is just about at
home in the water as it is on
the highway.
The same power plant and the
same controls make it a cinch to
operate, and twin props send it
through the water at
a brisk clip.
♪ ♪
It could be a wonderful way to
bypass traffic jams, but imagine
a rear-end collision in 40
fathoms of water.
♪ ♪
♪♪
[elevator bell]
Yup.
Little choices make
a big difference.
Like delicious fruits
and veggies.
However You Healthy.
Naked.
(Burke)
At Farmers, we've seen almost
everything,
so we know how to
cover almost anything.
Even Rooftop Parking.
Strange forces at work?
Only if you're referring to
gravity-and we covered it.
Talk to Farmers.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
I've got to tell you
something important.
It's NOT going to be easy.
Quicksilver earns you unlimited
1.5% cash back
on every purchase, everywhere.
Actually,
that's super easy.
My bad.
At Hilton.com,
I can choose from all their
different hotel brands...
Like a DoubleTree
for my cousins.
A Homewood Suites
for my uncle.
A Hampton for
my sister and her kids.
And the Waldorf Astoria
Beverly Hills for me.
Can I get a..?
Thank you.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
Book at Hilton.com
I'm not hungry!
You're having one more bite
No!
One more bite!
♪
Kraft. For the win win.
I had a heart problem.
I was told to begin my
Aspirin regimen,
and I just didn't listen.
Until I almost lost my life.
My doctors again ordered
me to take Aspirin,
and I do.
Be sure to talk to your doctor
before you begin an
Aspirin regimen.
Listen to the doctor.
Take it seriously.
♪ I'm tasting olives... ♪
♪ Roasted pine nuts... ♪
♪ Mmm this red pepper... ♪
♪ That's spicy stuff... ♪
Fresh flavor. Feel good food.
Sabra Hummus.
♪ I just had Sabra Hummus and
now I feel good! ♪
From the start, the C-Class
was ahead of its time.
Still, we never stopped
making it stronger.
Faster.
Smarter.
Because to be the best,
is to never ever stop
making it better.
There's never been
a better time
to become part of the
Mercedes-Benz family.
Visit the Mercedes-Benz
Spring Event
before April 30th
for exceptional lease
and financing offers
on the 2019 C 300.
It's almost like, which one
is not like the other?
Because these two actually go in
the water, where that one just
kind of goes near the water and
hangs around and has mint juleps
and things like that.
>> With great style.
>> With great style--certainly
better style than either
of these.
All right, which one do you want
to start with?
>> Well, Jay, let's start with
the Amphicar.
>> Okay.
>> Five years ago, one of these
cars could have been purchased
for about $55,000.
And today, you'd pay
about $75,000.
>> That high, huh?
>> Absolutely.
>> Okay.
>> Now let's go to
the Schwimmwagen.
Because of their rarity,
and because of the interest
they've always been
very valuable.
Five years ago, one of these
would have been about $150,000.
>> Wow, okay.
>> And today, $185,000 would not
be out of the question.
>> Wow, I didn't think it was
anywhere near that. Okay.
Well, let's go over to my baby,
the Crane-Simplex.
>> One of these, about five
years ago, would have cost
about $150,000.
Today, it would cost
about $225,000.
>> Okay.
>> So the winner of our
five-year appreciation
sweepstakes...
>> Ah, okay.
>> The Crane-Simplex.
>> Well, I finally won
one of these.
Thank you.
>> Congratulations, sir.
>> Man, it took two seasons.
>> Can't rush into these things.
>> Jeez.
>> [laughing]
[energetic music]
♪ ♪
>> Okay, I'm sliding around.
The car I'm driving right now is
a 2016 Mustang GT.
It's got the five-liter engine.
It's got a six-speed,
manual gearbox.
It's got the Track Pack, with
better handling and control.
A traction control is a system
that helps limit tire slip on
slippery surfaces.
On most modern cars, it's an
option you can turn on or off.
I feel the car sliding under me.
As you can see, I don't have it
on right now.
[engine revving]
Now, traction control doesn't
mean you won't slip.
It just limits the amount of
slipping you do.
Sometimes it's fun to go old
school, and that's exactly what
we're doing today.
♪ ♪
Fun hanging the tail end out
like this.
♪ ♪
I think I like the traction
control off.
♪ ♪
Now, to show you how water can
affect car performance, we set
up a little figure-eight wet
course with NBC executives we
have to avoid.
'Cause there's nothing like a
good contest, I've challenged my
old buddy Alonzo Bodden to an
old-fashioned traction-off race.
Hey, Alonzo.
>> How you doing, Jay?
>> Good seeing you.
Now, a simple wet course is
child's play, and since Alonzo
and I are pretty experienced
drivers, I thought we'd make
things a little
more challenging.
I tell you what we're gonna do.
We want to show you what it's
like to drive while impaired.
Now, the folks at Ford have
created this drunk driving suit:
goggles to blur the vision and
body weight that mimics the
effect of being under the
influence of alcohol.
And guess what.
We're gonna put it on.
Jim, come on in.
Now, what is your title?
What do you do?
>> I'm the manager of Ford's
Driving Skills
for Life program.
>> Okay, so you teach young kids
about the dangers of
driving impaired.
>> Impaired, distracted--also
teach them 'em advanced driving
skills they didn't learn in
Driver's Ed.
But impaired driving's
extremely important.
>> Let's bring in the drunk
driving suit.
>> Come on in, Nolan.
>> What do we have here?
>> Nolan will put goggles on him
that simulate the...
>> Let's start with
these goggles.
>> Okay.
>> Now let's put some weights
down on your ankles.
>> You do what you got to do,
my friend.
Have you put these on, Jay?
'Cause I'm not sure where you
went. [laughing]
>> And how many drinks are we
talking about here?
>> Well, .08 is typically around
four in an hour if--beers,
for example.
>> Four drinks in an hour.
>> Four beers in an hour.
>> All right.
>> You are suited up.
>> Flexibility's thrown off
a little bit there.
So now you're all set.
>> Okay.
>> Now, in real life, Alonzo and
I don't drink at all, so this
should be interesting.
>> All right, let's do it.
>> I'm getting out of the way.
>> I'm good.
These are heavily insured,
I'm guessing.
>> Good guess.
>> [laughing]
We're ready to go.
>> I'm here with Deputy
Sheriff RJ.
He's hosing down the track and
hitting Alonzo with some water.
Let's see what happens.
>> Hey, tell the officer
I'm a close, personal friend
of Jay Leno
in case there's any trouble.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Wow.
Really?
>> And go.
Okay, moving very cautiously.
Okay, I think he's--I think he--
he went outside the, uh...
[buzzer]
Okay, this is not good.
>> I'm seeing a lot of cones.
>> Well, he hasn't hit
anything yet.
Okay, maybe the idea of traction
control really doesn't work
when you're only going
two miles an hour.
♪ ♪
>> I don't know where
the course went.
>> He's not even on
the track now.
[buzzer]
He appears to be lost.
[laughing]
Okay, ran over a cone.
[buzzer]
>> Hey, there's something wrong
with this car--not me.
I'm fine.
I'm gonna try this direction.
I'm between cones.
I don't know which ones.
[laughing]
>> Okay, I'm gonna see
if I can find him.
>> I think I won.
>> How do you think you did?
>> Fantastic.
It looks like everything's
still standing.
>> That's 'cause you weren't on
the course at all.
>> All right, Jay,
Mr. Expert Driver,
Mr. This Is My Show,
how about you give it a shot?
>> I'll give it a shot.
>> Yeah, yeah.
You try the helmet and the
goggles and the clown.
>> I can't see anything.
>> [laughing]
Give him a little more water.
There you go.
Three, two, one.
Jay Leno, professional driver.
Boom. [buzzer]
We didn't need that cone,
did we?
>> [chuckling]
>> You know, from the way he
does this, I think he might
drink and drive on
a regular basis.
He's actually pretty good.
[buzzer]
Well, I may have spoke too soon.
[laughs]
>> No sure where I'm going here.
>> Yeah.
Now he's speeding it up.
[tires squealing]
Now he's working.
Oh, Officer, did you see that?
That can't be legal.
>> Okay, I mean, this is about
as dangerous as it gets.
[engine roaring]
>> So, Officer, if you saw a man
driving like that,
how quickly would you
pull him over?
>> Pretty quickly.
Well, Jay, I'm gonna have to say
I'm impressed.
You drove half the course in
half the time.
So I'm not sure if that's a win
or not.
>> I don't know.
Boy, this is...
>> This is really scary to think
people are this impaired when
they're driving.
>> I can't even imagine.
>> I mean...
>> It's unbelievable.
I tell you, I need you a drink.
>> This is scary.
>> I mean, these are amazing
driver aids--
traction control,
stability control,
but it's still up to
the driver, isn't it?
>> Yeah.
>> You only do so much.
>> None of that equipment
that's put in the cars helps
if you're drunk.
>> Right.
>> Don't do it.
>> Don't be Alonzo.
>> Jay Leno is a very impressive
drunk driver.
However, I have superior drunk
basketball skills.
>> [laughing]
>> All right.
>> For more cool cars, go to
jaylenosgrage.cnbcprime.com.
The Lexus ES.
Every curve, every
innovation, every feeling.
A product of mastery.
Lease the 2019 ES 350 for
$389 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
♪ I'm tasting olives... ♪
♪ Roasted pine nuts... ♪
♪ Mmm this red pepper... ♪
♪ That's spicy stuff... ♪
Fresh flavor. Feel good food.
Sabra Hummus.
♪ I just had Sabra Hummus and
now I feel good! ♪
GLAD YOU'RE BACK
HOW YOU FEELING?
♪ ♪ ♪
(BOTH) EXHAUSTED.
BUT FINALLY BEING ABLE TO MAKE
THAT VOLUNTEER TRIP HAPPEN
WAS... AWESOME.
AWESOME.
YOU HAVE TO SCRUB.
WHAT DO THEY...
THEY USE FOR WASHING.
♪ ♪ ♪
LET'S DO IT EVERY YEAR.
WE'LL DO IT EVERY YEAR.
I THOUGHT YOU'D SAY THAT -
LET'S DO IT.
♪ ♪ ♪
SEE HOW INVESTING WITH A J.P.
MORGAN ADVISOR CAN HELP YOU.
VISIT YOUR LOCAL CHASE BRANCH.
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
-♪ Just like any other family ♪
♪ The house, kids,
they're living the dream ♪
♪ And here comes
the wacky new maid ♪
-Maid?
Uh, I'm not the...
-♪ Is she an alien,
is she a spy? ♪
♪ She's always here,
someone tell us why ♪
-♪ Why, oh, why ♪
-♪ She's not the maid
we wanted ♪
-Because I'm not the maid!
-♪ But she's the maid we got ♪
-Again, I'm not the maid.
I protect your home and auto.
-Hey, Campbells.
Who's your new maid?
that's pretty much a limitless
supply of fuel, isn't it?
Well, a company is doing
exactly that.
nanoFlowcell has created
the QUANT E,
a supercar that runs on
Flowcell technology.
Basically, without getting too
technical, it runs on a battery
powered by two tanks,
a negative and a positive,
filled with ionic liquids--
salt water.
The reaction creates
electricity,
which powers the car.
Now, to be clear, you can't
just dump in some seawater.
These are highly sophisticated
electrolyte fluids.
It has zero emissions,
and unlike an electric car,
it refuels much like you would
an ordinary car.
Now, the technology is
fascinating and has a ton of
potential, yet most experts are
still a bit skeptical.
Still, the car is impressive.
Modern and sleek with gull wing
doors, the QUANT E delivers
920 horsepower,
has a top speed of
218 miles per hour,
and can go 370 miles
on a single charge.
However, these claims are
unconfirmed, so you might want
to take it with a grain of salt.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
This is what I love about
California: we're just about an
hour from my garage where it was
80 degrees, and now I'm up to my
wheels in snow.
Actually, I would be up to my
wheels in snow if this thing
had wheels.
[engine roaring]
But it doesn't.
It's pretty cool.
You can go anywhere
in this thing.
♪ ♪
And the nice thing is,
there's no traffic.
♪ ♪
Nissan's new concept car,
the Winter Warrior,
is nothing more than
a stock Murano with
one small difference:
enormous, heavy-duty tracks
instead of wheels.
This would be fun to do to your
mom's car.
"Mom, can I borrow the car?"
"Okay, be careful."
Take it over to your friend's
house--you put these tracks on
it, climb a couple of mountains,
and bring it back.
"What? No, I don't know, Mom,
soccer practice."
♪ ♪
Yee-haw!
Fun with your mom's car.
♪ ♪
When asked why would they make
this car, Nissan responded,
"Because we can," which is...
good enough answer for me.
Looks like Frosty the Snowman
down there.
When I was six, I waited two
hours in line at the mall to
meet him, and then he split
right before they got to me.
Hey, Frosty, here's a taste
of your own medicine.
See how you like it!
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
Take that, Frosty!
[bleep] [bleep]!
[spits]
I think I like the
80 degrees better.
So what is the importance
of water to the automobile?
All right, this is stupid fun.
It can generate power....
So we're looking at
20,000 horsepower.
Okay, now we're talking.
Shape its design...
All sorts of ship-like cues
throughout the whole thing.
Influence technology.
It can even save lives...
Pistons move up and down,
and that pushes the water.
>> Exactly.
>> As well as endanger them.
>> That can't be legal.
>> But just remember, any time
you mix water and cars...
>> Bon voyage.
>> It's gonna be interesting.
Thank you!
>> It's time for me to go home.
Hello?
Anyone?