>>> PEOPLE ASK ME WHAT IS YOUR
FAVORITE CANNABIS STOCK.
IT IS CANOPY
THEY HAVE THE MONEY AND THEY'VE
GOT THE SKILL.
I LIKE TO SAY THERE IS ALWAYS A
BULL MARKET SOMEWHERE AND I'LL
FIND IT FOR YOU HERE ON "MAD
MONEY.
I'M JIM CRAMER AND I'LL SEE YOU
TOMORROW
- [whistles]
male announcer:
Tonight...
- A big offer
is coming your way.
announcer: The million-dollar
dream is alive.
- I don't like the banker,
and I feel lucky.
announcer: And preschool
fitness instructor,
Missy Silverman, is going...
- You know those little toys
that you wind up?
That's what you remind me of.
announcer: For the gold.
- I win. I'm a winner.
Yes, look at me!
I say no deal!
No deal, Howie!
announcer:
Will this pint-size powerhouse
take home the biggest prize?
- Banker, shmanker.
No deal!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
announcer:
From Universal Orlando Resort,
get ready for the ultimate
TV thrill ride.
It's "Deal or No Deal."
♪ ♪
- I'm Howie Mandel, and
welcome to "Deal or No Deal."
[cheers and applause]
So tonight, our player is in
for the battle of their lives.
They will battle the banker,
they will battle that board,
and battle for $1 million.
It's the ultimate game of risk
and a fight where they need
some serious backup,
and I never go anywhere
without my backup.
Ladies, please.
♪ ♪
Hello, ladies.
all: Hello, Howie.
- It's good to see you.
Let's get started and meet
our player, Missy Silverman.
[cheers and applause]
There you are.
- Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Howie!
- Hi.
- Hi!
- Hello. How are you?
- Oh, my gosh.
It's so nice to meet you.
- Wow.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- Hi! Hi!
Oh, my gosh!
Hi!
- What an adorable bundle
of energy you are.
Tell me about yourself.
- Oh, my gosh.
Okay, my name's
Missy Silverman.
- Right.
- I'm from Philadelphia.
- Okay.
- And I teach--
[cheers and applause]
Philly!
- Phillies fans?
- They are.
- I teach preschool fitness
to little kids.
- Preschool fitness, wow.
- Yes.
- Jumping jacks, jogging.
- Wow.
- Cha-cha.
- Cha-cha, because preschoolers
don't move enough.
You get them moving more.
- I do.
Yes, it's so much fun.
- That's wonderful.
Tell me about
your personal life.
- Okay, so I have two
amazing teenagers.
- Right.
- And I am married 23 years.
- Congratulations.
You look too young for that.
- Oh, I feel young.
- And if you should win
$1 million,
what are the kind of things
you'd want to do?
- I've been a mom for 19 years,
and I take care of my parents,
and I work full time,
so if I win the money,
I need a girl vacation.
A girl vacation!
- So you've been giving
and being for others.
- Oh, Howie, yes.
- So tonight is all about you
and getting stuff that's
for you.
I get it.
So with a million dollars,
the things
with a million dollars,
you said a girl trip.
- Yes.
- Anything else?
- Oh, well, college
for my kids.
- College,
so it's for the family
and for the future
and for trips.
- Yes.
- Are you ready to play?
- I'm ready, I'm ready!
- Okay, let's go!
- Oh, hi!
Okay.
- All right.
There are 26 lovely ladies
holding 26 different cases,
and in each of those cases
is a different amount of money,
randomly packed
by a third party,
so we don't know
what's in any case.
We do know that the largest
amount of money is $1 million
all the way down to a penny.
You just have to pick a case.
Are you a lucky person?
- I'm so lucky.
I enter every contest
imaginable,
and I win concert tickets
and ice cream for my entire
business, my family business.
- What business are you in?
- Oh, my husband and I
have a hand car wash.
- Okay, and is that business
doing well?
- Yes, yes.
- Okay, good.
I want to tell you something.
Our producers knew--I guess
they had spoken to you--
that you wanted to travel.
Well, one of these cases has
a very special prize inside,
and if you open it
before you take the deal,
the prize is gonna be yours.
Are you feeling lucky?
- Yes!
Oh, my gosh!
- Which case do you want?
- Okay, I want case number 17!
17.
- 17, that's Ashley.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
Thanks, Ashley.
- Hi, thank you.
You're gorgeous.
Yay!
Mwah. Hi.
- You feeling it?
- Yes.
- All right, so let's find out
if 17's got a million in it.
You know how we do it?
- Yes.
- By opening those.
Whatever's in those
is not in yours.
Let's start by opening up
six cases.
- Okay. Number 24!
- Kizzi.
- Low, low, low, low, low.
- Kizzi, open your case.
- Yes!
- Good.
- Yes! Yes!
Come on!
Yes!
- Yes.
- Low.
- Five more.
- 12! 12.
- That's Sarati.
Sarati, open the case.
- Yes, yes!
Oh, my God, I'm so happy.
- You're making
everybody happy.
Four more cases.
- Oh, gosh. Okay.
- 14!
- Number 14 is Olga.
- 14.
- Olga, open your case.
- Oh.
[crowd groans]
- It's a little bit of a hit.
$750,000 is off the plate.
That means that this case...
- The million's in there!
- Doesn't have $750,000.
It means it could
still have $1 million.
- Okay. Okay.
- Three more cases.
- Six, six, six!
- Six. Megan, open your case.
- Okay, okay.
- That's good. That's good.
- Okay.
- Got to find
that special prize.
- I'm looking!
- I know.
- Okay, number 19!
- That's Natasha.
Natasha, open your case.
[all groaning]
- $200,000.
- Howie.
- Okay, but there's still a lot
of big amounts up there.
One more case.
- Number three.
- That's Katie.
- Low, low, low.
- Katie is the last one
in this round.
It would be nice to close
the round with a prize.
That would be nice.
- Please. That would be nice.
- Open the case.
- Girls' trip, girls' trip.
- Oh, please.
Yes, yes, yes!
That's good.
- That's good.
- That's good. Thank you.
- You still have huge money
on the board.
You still got
the big amounts there.
We want you to go home
with prizes.
We want you
to go home with money.
We want you to have the time
that you now deserve
for yourself.
Everybody wants that.
- Please, for sure. Yes.
- Except one person.
That lady up there.
That lady wants you to go home
with as little as possible.
She wants to buy your case
and send you out of here now.
- I forgot about her.
- You forgot about her?
- Banker, shmanker.
- All right.
- Be nice.
[crowd jeering]
Be nice, be nice.
- She said
she will not be nice.
She's not here to be nice.
She's here to be shrewd.
She's a business person,
so she is only going to do
whatever it takes
to get you to leave here
for as little as possible.
- I am not leaving.
[applause]
- Well,
she's gonna make you an offer
to buy this case right now.
- Okay.
- All right, your first offer
is $19,000.
Listen to me.
$19,000.
She will give you that
right now,
take that case,
and you're on your way.
There is also a little twist
in "Deal or No Deal" 2.0,
where you have
the opportunity
for one counteroffer
in the game.
You can counter.
If she accepts it,
she gets the case,
you get the money,
and you go home.
If she says no deal,
you play on.
In this case, playing on
is opening up
another five cases,
and remember,
there's also a prize in there.
You say you're lucky.
- I am.
- She said,
"If she's so lucky,
let's see
if she can find the prize."
So I'm gonna ask you,
Missy Silverman,
deal or no deal?
[crowd shouting]
- No!
- I don't like the banker.
No deal!
I don't like her.
- You know those little toys
that you wind up?
That's what you remind me of.
- I know, that's funny.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- 23!
- Anne Julia, open your case.
- Low. Low, low, low, low.
Yes!
[cheering]
I'm so happy.
- We have four more cases
to open,
and we'll open those four
when we come back.
♪ ♪
- [whistles] Wake up, banker!
- Whoa, whoa!
announcer: The battle
has only just begun.
- She does not like spunky.
- She needs to lighten up.
announcer: And only one
of these women
will go home happy.
- She's not looking thrilled.
- I want more money,
and I don't like the banker,
and I feel lucky.
[cheers and applause]
- Whoa!
- Whoo!
♪♪
Every day,
visionaries are creating
the future.
♪♪
So, every day,
we put our latest technology
and unrivaled network to work.
♪♪
The United States
Postal Service makes
more e-commerce
deliveries to homes
than anyone else
in the country.
♪♪
Because the future only
happens with people
who really know how
to deliver it.
Let's see, ALEVE is
proven better on pain
Because the future only
happens with people
than Tylenol Extra Strength.
And last longer
with fewer pills.
So why am I still
thinking about this?
I'll take Aleve.
ALEVE.
Proven better on pain.
AI unlocks the art of science.
When you open a bottle of beer,
I don't think many people
actually know
the level of science
that's filled into that bottle.
Back in time, it took Carlsberg
several years
to produce a new beer.
But using
Microsoft Artificial
Intelligence,
we will be able to detect
new flavors in a split second
and develop better beers
faster.
With AI, we redefine
what's possible.
So cheers!
[dramatic music]
[cheers and applause]
- All right, welcome back
to "Deal or No Deal."
This is Missy Silverman.
She's dreaming
of a getaway trip
for her and her friends.
She's a mom.
She's a wife.
She's a teacher.
She's a business owner.
You got a lot going on.
- Oh, my gosh, I do.
- And you say you're very,
very lucky.
- I am.
- Right, you win every contest.
- I try, yes.
- Okay.
If you're just joining us,
there is a prize,
an added prize
in one of the cases,
and you're supposed
to be the lucky one,
so find the prize, Missy.
- Okay.
Oh, my.
- Four cases to open.
- Let me see.
I hate picking them, because
then the girls have to go,
and they're so pretty.
Okay.
- You want to feel good
about it?
When they go, they get
to take their shoes off.
- Ah!
Okay, okay.
[laughter]
All right, girls, 22!
- Anchal.
- Low, low, low, low, low, low.
- Open the case.
- Yes, yes, yes,
oh, my gosh!
Thank you, 22.
- It's like a really pretty
energizer bunny.
Okay, three more cases.
- Okay, four! Four!
- That's Brenda.
- Oh, low, low, low, low, low.
- Or prize, a prize.
- Or a vacation.
- Open the case.
[all groaning]
- Not good.
- It's all right.
- The million dollars
is off the board,
but look at this.
There is a block
on the board--
that bottom right
goes $300,000,
$400,000, and $1/2 million.
That's huge.
- That's a lot of money, yes.
- You would get everything
that you wanted
with any of those amounts
of money, right?
- It would be a dream
come true.
- So all your dreams
are still on that board.
That's a huge amount of money.
Keep that block together,
and we're going places.
Two more cases.
- Number five!
Five!
- That's Lani.
Open the case.
- Low, low.
Oh, low.
- Oh, no.
- Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
- She fooled you. Oh, my.
- One more case.
- Okay, number ten!
- Number ten is Vaeda.
Open your case.
- Please, please, please,
please.
Yay!
Yay, yay, yay!
- Whoa!
- Whoo!
- Was that a cartwheel?
- That was a cartwheel.
- Wow!
- I'm so excited
I'm doing cartwheels.
- Oh, my. Wow.
You got a penny
and stuck the landing.
I think that's wonderful.
All right,
here's your arch nemesis.
[crowd jeering]
- Oh, no.
- She says one word
comes to mind
when she looks at you,
and that is spunky.
[laughter]
- Spunky, baby.
[applause]
- Oh, oh.
She's saying
she does not like spunky.
[crowd murmuring]
- Well, she needs
to lighten up.
[laughter]
- Okay.
You knocked out the million,
so she's dropping this offer
to $10,000.
Listen to me.
$10,000 is a lot of money.
You've been here
for a couple of minutes,
you know, boom, $10,000.
Nobody gets that kind of money.
You also have an opportunity
to counter-offer.
If it's a reasonable
counteroffer, she may take it,
you sell your case,
and you go home,
or you can continue on
and open up another four cases.
These are big decisions,
but you brought people you know
with you.
Let's meet your supporters.
- Okay.
- Hi.
- Who are you?
- I'm Jill.
I've been best friends
with Missy my entire life.
We went to elementary school
together.
We went to middle school
together, high school,
college, we got married.
Not together, but...
[laughs]
- She's my best friend.
- She was the first person
there when my water broke
when I was having a baby,
and she is lucky,
and she is gonna win.
- Wow.
You are?
- Renee.
- Hi, Renee.
- Hi.
Missy and I have been friends
forever as well.
I love her energy.
She is a caregiver.
Her father lost his sight,
and she is there for him
every day.
There's no one more deserving
than her family and her.
- That's so nice.
And you are?
- Hi, I'm Jill also.
I've been best friends
with Marissa
since I was five years old,
and one thing Marissa didn't
tell you, she is an only child.
She has taken care
of her parents her entire life.
She is giving.
She is kind.
No one deserves
this opportunity
more than my best friend,
no one.
[cheers and applause]
- I love them.
- And they love you.
Is this your family right here?
- Yes.
- Are you proud of your mom?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, extremely.
- Yeah, they are.
So everybody's proud of you.
Everybody speaks highly of you,
but they've got an important
decision to make right now.
Talk amongst yourselves.
What do you want to do?
- Okay. What should we do?
- Look at the board.
You're not ready to go.
- Yeah, no.
Some really big numbers.
- We're gonna play the game.
- No deal.
- No deal, no deal.
- It's still a lot
of money, Howie.
- It is a lot of money, but
I'm gonna ask you the question.
Missy Silverman,
deal or no deal?
- Oh, Howie.
[crowd shouting]
- Just play it.
- Okay.
No deal!
No deal, no deal!
- You got four cases to open.
You could still find
that special prize in there.
Let's keep going.
- 16!
16.
- 16 is Jessica Lee.
- I hope it's low, low, low.
- Jessica Lee, open your case.
- Ooh.
- Oh!
- That was the worst case.
- Oh, my Lord.
- But you still got a block,
$300,000 and $400,000.
Either one of those
is the dream, right?
- Oh, yeah.
- Okay.
Three more cases.
- Number one!
Number one.
- Soraya.
Soraya, she's asking
for a low amount or a vacation.
- Low amount. She's not asking
me to do a cartwheel,
because I can't do that,
but a low amount I could do.
- No cartwheel.
- She'll do a cartwheel
if you have what she wants.
- I will, I will.
- I really would love that.
Ready?
- Yes.
- Okay. Please low.
- Vacation, low, low, low.
Yeah! That's good.
[cheers and applause]
That's good!
- Yeah!
- I had to do it for you!
Yes, thank you.
- Two more.
- That's good.
All right, you're gorgeous,
I hate to see you go,
but number nine!
Nine!
- Patricia.
- Low, low, low, low, low.
- Patricia, open the case.
- Okay, that's all right.
- Ohh!
- You kept the $300,000
and the $400,000 still in play.
Don't break that block.
You have one more case.
- 21!
- That's Malika. Malika.
- 21, low, low, low, low.
- Open the case.
- Left side, left side.
Yes! That's good!
That's good.
- Wow, that is fantastic.
You realize there could be
$300,000 in this case,
or there could be $400,000
in this case,
which means a big offer
is coming your way
when we come back.
♪ ♪
Can we know what the goal is?
- Yeah, to get the $400,000.
announcer: Huge cash
is still up for grabs...
- No deal, Howie.
No deal!
Oh, my God.
announcer: But that's not all
Missy is looking for.
- Please, please, please,
please.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
GLAD YOU'RE BACK
HOW YOU FEELING?
♪ ♪ ♪
(BOTH) EXHAUSTED.
BUT FINALLY BEING ABLE TO MAKE
THAT VOLUNTEER TRIP HAPPEN
WAS... AWESOME.
AWESOME.
YOU HAVE TO SCRUB.
WHAT DO THEY...
THEY USE FOR WASHING.
♪ ♪ ♪
LET'S DO IT EVERY YEAR.
WE'LL DO IT EVERY YEAR.
I THOUGHT YOU'D SAY THAT -
LET'S DO IT.
♪ ♪ ♪
SEE HOW INVESTING WITH A J.P.
MORGAN ADVISOR CAN HELP YOU.
VISIT YOUR LOCAL CHASE BRANCH.
IF YOU HAVE A GARDEN YOU KNOW,
WEEDS ARE LOWDOWN
LITTLE SCOUNDRELS.
DON'T STOOP TO THEIR LEVEL.
DRAW THE LINE WITH THE
ROUNDUP SURE SHOT WAND.
IT EXTENDS WITH A
PROTECTIVE SHIELD
AND TARGETS WEEDS
MORE PRECISELY.
IT LETS YOU KILL WHAT'S BAD
RIGHT DOWN TO THE ROOT
WHILE GUARDING THE GOOD.
ROUNDUP SURE SHOT WAND.
GOT WEEDS IN YOUR GRASS TOO?
TRY ROUNDUP FOR LAWNS.
KILLS WEEDS, NOT THE LAWN.
ROUNDUP BRAND.
TRUSTED FOR OVER 40 YEARS.
The Lexus ES.
Every curve, every
innovation, every feeling.
A product of mastery.
Lease the 2019 ES 350 for
$389 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
[farmers bell]
(Driver)
Relax, it's just a bug.
That's not a bug,
that's not a bug!
(Burke)
Hit and Drone.
Seen it, covered it.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
[dramatic music]
[cheers and applause]
- Welcome back
to "Deal or No Deal."
This is Missy Silverman.
You were about to get an offer.
You've turned down
a lot of money already.
That was a good round.
You've got a safety net there.
You may have $300,000
or $400,000
in number 17 right there.
She's not looking thrilled.
- I forgot about her.
- We're awaiting her call.
[crowd murmuring]
- Hello.
Oh.
- [exhales]
- Okay, all right.
That's surprising.
- Oh, surprising good?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Okay.
Surprising good.
I'll tell you why,
because she was saying
you think you're lucky.
She thinks she's lucky.
- I am, I feel lucky.
- She's putting a little faith
in your luck.
- Oh, that's nice.
- So the offer went up
to $32,000.
[cheers and applause]
She said,
"I think she might be lucky,
but is she the kind of person
that will press her luck?"
- Oh.
- You can walk out now
with $32,000,
you can counter-offer,
or you can say no deal.
If you said no deal
or a counteroffer
was not accepted,
you have to open up
three cases.
Look at the board.
There are two huge amounts
and three cases to open,
so how lucky are you?
How strategic are you?
Do you want to counter?
- That's a lot of money,
$32,000.
- Huge amount of money.
- Years ago, we had a fire
at our family car wash.
Our business had burned down.
- Aw.
- To the ground. My gosh.
And that money really can help,
but there's still $400,000
on the board
and $300,000 on the board,
and I'm a fighter.
I am a fighter.
I think I might keep fighting.
- Absolutely!
Absolutely!
- Keep going.
- Your daughter's talking
to you.
What are you saying?
- I think she should
keep going.
- You think she should
You don't think she should
counter,
you don't think--
- No, I don't--no.
- Is your mom a fighter?
Do you think she's a fighter?
- Yeah.
- A fighter and a winner.
- "A fighter and a winner,"
your husband said.
- Keep going, keep going.
- Keep going.
- You have a goal,
you have a goal.
- She has a goal?
- And it's not your business.
- Oh, it's not my business.
Oh, so you have
an amount in mind?
- No, no, no, no,
not an amount, a goal.
- I have a goal.
We have a goal.
- Can we know what the goal is?
- Yeah, to get the $400,000.
Yes! Yes!
- Okay.
- That's the goal.
- Yes!
- Missy Silverman,
deal or no deal?
[crowd shouting]
- No way!
- No.
- No deal, Howie!
No deal.
- Wow.
Stay away
from those two cases.
- Okay, number 26!
- Michelle, open the case.
- Low, low, please,
please, please.
- You got the prize,
you got the prize!
- [cheering]
We're going away!
- By opening the case
that's holding
the Princess Cruises logo,
you have won a cruise
to one of Princess Cruises'
380 destinations
that span
over seven continents.
They are known to be the best
global premium cruise line.
Missy, discover the world
and relax at sea.
Congratulations.
You can go anywhere
with the girls.
You got the girls' trip.
- We're going on a cruise!
[cheers and applause]
Oh, my gosh. I'm so happy!
- Two more cases.
- Okay, two.
- Taylor.
- A little amount.
- Taylor, open your case.
- Oh, please.
- Small amount, left side.
- Little, left side, left side.
Yay! That's good.
Oh, that's good.
- That's great.
- Thank you.
- That's great, one more.
15!
- 15, that's Madi.
Madi, open your case.
- Oh, I can't look.
I'm nervous.
- So am I.
- Low, low, low, low.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
I'm freaking out.
- That's a great board.
- Oh, yay.
- You think you're
freaking out?
I think she's freaking out.
That's because the game
is going great for you,
not so great for her.
- Hello?
Hello?
- [whistles]
Wake up, banker!
- Whoa, whoa.
- Did she just do that?
- That was--hang on.
- Let's go, girl!
- What was that?
You scared me.
I didn't know what that--
did that come out of you?
[laughter]
How do you do that?
- Oh, boy.
Oh, my gosh.
- Right.
Okay. All right.
Okay, there's eight cases left
that have not been opened.
Two of them have huge amounts,
which means you have
a 25% chance
of walking out of here
with at least $300,000.
[cheers and applause]
You do,
if you continue to play on,
have to open up two cases,
so it's a little precarious,
but you're in good shape.
She understands
that you're in good shape.
She knows the board, and
that's why this next offer--
- Uh-huh.
- "Uh-huh."
- In good shape.
- $53,000,
and you still have
an opportunity to counteroffer.
- No, no.
- There's so much going on.
- No. No, no, no,
look at the board, okay?
You had a goal.
You're in a really
good position,
and that number
is not high enough.
- It's a high number, though.
- Don't take it.
- Honey?
- I think you should
keep going.
- Okay.
- Okay, well.
- So I'm gonna ask you
the question.
Missy Silverman,
deal or no deal?
[crowd shouting]
- Okay, Howie.
No deal!
- No deal.
Two cases to go.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Two cases to go.
Only two big amounts.
A little precarious,
but very exciting.
We'll find out what she picks
when you come back.
♪ ♪
- Hi!
announcer: There are only
eight cases left.
- Look at her board.
- Yeah.
- Look at that board.
- The question now is,
will your luck hold on?
announcer:
Has Missy gone too far?
- I'm scared.
I'm scared.
- I'm scared for you.
- I know.
announcer:
Or does she have the banker
right she wants her?
- Oh, it is about to get
real, young lady.
NAYSAYER SAID NO ONE
WOULD SUBSCRIBE TO A CAR
THE WAY THEY
SUBSCRIBE TO MOVIES.
WE DON'T FOLLOW THE NAYSAYERS.
♪ ♪ ♪
So Kim, you going for our big
Drive Safe & Save discount?
Yup, using the app. I've been
quite vigilant.
Sharon says step on it. The
meeting's started.
OK, write her back 'Dear Sharon,
don't mess with my discount!'
Faster Mommy, I gotta go to the
bathroom.
I do too honey, but we're gonna
hold it for Mommy's discount.
Easy, easy!
But you're in labor?
Don't mess with my discount!
Uh hem.
Get a discount up to 30%
with Drive Safe & Save
from State Farm.
I've got to tell you something.
With the Capital One
Venture card
you earn unlimited double miles
on every purchase, every day.
Not just airline purchases?
Everything.
Hey, how'd you get in here?
Cross-checking.
Nice.
What's in your wallet...
Oh, c'mon!
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM SAYS
YOU CAN'T MAKE A
400 HORSEPOWER SEDAN,
THAT'S ALSO
ENVIRONMENTALLY CONSCIOUS.
WE DON'T FOLLOW
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM.
♪ ♪ ♪
[dramatic music]c]
[cheers and applause]
- Welcome back
to "Deal or No Deal."
This is Missy Silverman.
Before the break,
you turned down $53,000.
You've won your dream trip.
- We've won our dream trip.
- Look at that board.
$300,000 and $400,000
are very good things.
- Yes.
- Even if you knock out
one of those big amounts,
the next offer's going down.
- Oh.
- Just stay away from those
two big amounts.
- Okay.
- Two cases to open.
- Case number 18!
- 18.
- I can't look.
I can't look.
- Elissa, open your case.
- Oh, please, please.
- Good.
- That's okay.
That's okay.
- It's really good.
- That's okay.
- One more case.
- Okay.
20! 20, 20.
- Amanza.
This is a very
important case.
If you can stay away from
the $300,000 and the $400,000,
you're looking
at a very big offer.
- Okay, I'm hoping, Howie.
- So, Amanza, just stay away
from those two amounts.
- Please, please.
- You have the best energy.
Just put some into this case
and it's gonna work.
- Oh, please, low, low, low...
[all chanting]
Low, low, low.
- Open the case.
- Low, low, low!
- Please!
- There you go.
- I'm scared.
[cheers and applause]
- That is good!
- That's good.
- Not only is that great--
if you decide to play on,
it's only one case at a time.
There are only six cases left.
You have a one
out of three chance
of walking out of here
with $300,000.
You still have not used
your counteroffer.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
- You're doing great.
- You are.
- You're doing really,
really great.
- Okay.
- Let's just hear it,
and we'll talk.
- She said you did
what you had to do.
- Yep, oh, yeah.
- I don't know what that means,
but yes,
I did what I had to do.
- So therefore, she has to do
what she has to do.
- Oh, boy. Okay.
Oh, well...
- How hard was it,
when you think back,
to turn down $53,000?
- It was very, very hard
to turn down $53,000.
- It was very hard.
- Yes.
- So if that was hard,
what are you gonna do...
- Oh, no.
- With $77,000?
- Oh!
- No.
- Look at her board.
- Yeah.
- Look at that board.
- That's a pretty board.
- And now, she only does one
at a time.
- Right.
- One at a time!
- It's not even time
for the counteroffer.
- Mom, then you can do
a counteroffer for the--
- What do you say?
- I'm saying she should wait
to counter-offer until, like,
if she knocks
one of the bigger ones.
- Yeah.
- She still can lose one.
She can still lose one of
the $300,000 or the $400,000.
- He doesn't always agree
with her, so he agreed.
- This is the first time
they have agreed?
- It might be.
The force is with you.
I'd keep going.
- But you realize,
if she knocks out
and loses one of those amounts,
either the $300,000
or the $400,000,
there's no safety net.
- Don't play it safe.
- He's saying,
your son just said,
"Don't play it safe."
- I know,
but it's a lot of money.
- You came to play.
- You know, you do a lot
for everybody else.
- I do.
- The question is,
what do you want to do
for yourself,
Missy Silverman?
Deal or no deal?
[crowd shouting]
[all chanting]
One more case! One more case!
- No deal!
One more case!
Oh!
Oh, my gosh, I'm scared,
but I feel lucky.
- Yes!
- Oh, I'm scared.
- One case.
- Okay, one case.
- Just keep your safety net
employed.
- Okay, 11!
11!
- Brittany.
- I'm so scared.
Oh, my gosh.
- Brittany, do what you can,
open the case.
- $5, $5!
- Low, low.
- I'm feeling the pressure.
- Oh, please, low, low.
Low, low, low, low, please.
Oh, that's good!
[cheers and applause]
- Wow!
Big offer coming your way
when we come back.
- Yes!
♪ ♪
- Oh, my gosh,
it's so exciting.
announcer: Whether it's
walking on the beautiful beach
at Universal's Volcano Bay...
- This is gonna be fun!
announcer: Or heading down
a water slide...
- Whoo!
announcer: Missy Silverman
never stops moving.
Internet that puts
you in charge.
Alright boys, time to eat.
That handles anything.
[ crowd cheering ]
That protects
what's important.
And reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
(MEG VO)
I can see if my endometriosis
pain gets better...
Or I can...
(SHERRY VO)
I can just suck it up...
Or I can...
(DIANE VO)
I can tell myself tomorrow
will be different...
Or I can talk to
my gynecologist today!
(AVO)
You didn't choose to have
endometriosis...
but you can choose to ask
if ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA is specifically
developed for women
with moderate to severe
endometriosis pain.
In clinical trials,
ORILISSA was proven to reduce 3
common types of
endometriosis pain,
painful periods,
pelvic pain in between
periods,
and pain with sex.
Don't use ORILISSA if you are or
may be pregnant,
have osteoporosis,
severe liver disease, or are
taking drugs like
cyclosporine or gemfibrozil.
It may cause abnormal
liver tests.
ORILISSA may change your
periods, making it hard
to know if you are pregnant.
It does not prevent pregnancy.
Use birth control that does not
contain hormones.
ORILISSA may cause suicidal
thoughts or actions.
It may also cause bone loss.
Ask your gynecologist if
ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA. Made for endo pain.
One-millionth order.
Millionth order.
♪
There goes our first big order.
44, 45, 46...
How many of these
did they order?
Ooh, that's hot.
♪
You know, we could sell these.
Nah.
♪
We don't bake.
Opportunity.
What we deliver by delivering.
[dramatic music]
[cheers and applause]
- All right, welcome back
to "Deal or No Deal."
Missy Silverman,
mom, wife, business woman,
won a dream vacation.
You've got a big offer coming.
You said, during the commercial
break, what did you say to me?
"It doesn't feel real?"
- It does not feel real.
- Oh, it is about
to get real, young lady.
[phone ringing]
[crowd jeering]
- Oh, the banker.
- Hello.
Okay.
You said it was hard
to turn down $53,000.
- It was.
- You said it was harder
to turn down $77,000.
- That's a lot of money.
- It is a lot of money.
- Oh, no.
- There's a new offer.
- What is it?
I can't take it.
- You have to make
a decision...
- Oh!
- About $117,000 dollars.
[cheers and applause]
- Wow.
- Oh, that's so much money.
- It just got serious
over there.
- It's serious.
- One case to open.
No counteroffer.
You have tears.
Why do you have tears?
Talk to me.
- Because she deserves this.
She is a beaming light,
and she deserves everything.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, honey.
- Oh, honey, I love you.
- I love you, honey.
- Oh, my gosh.
- So we discussed this.
You still have
your counteroffer.
- Right.
- You still have two
really big numbers up there.
- Yes, really big.
- Oh, yes.
- We may have reached
her goal a little bit.
[laughter]
Forget the $117,000, whatever.
Think about those numbers
up there.
- Forget the $117,000?
- For a second!
We're having a discussion.
- I can't forget that.
That's a lot of money.
- Think about
what the next five years
you have in store for you.
- Oh, that's a lot.
- That's a lot.
- I know.
- What's in store for you
in the five years? I don't--
- My kids are going to college,
and I don't want them to
come out with a lot of loans,
and that would really help.
- That would do more than help.
- Yes.
- You guys.
- What are you guys discussing?
- I say she keeps going.
- Keeps going. No counter.
You're saying no counter.
- Not yet. I think she saves
the counter until--
if she loses one of those.
- Keep going, keep going.
- It's exactly what he said.
- One more, one more.
- Oh, Howie.
- Here's the thing.
Right now, the only guarantee
you have is $117,000,
but you also have luck,
you have risk,
and you have $300,000
and $400,000
left in the game, so...
- Oh, gosh.
Oh.
- I'm gonna ask you.
Missy Silverman,
the biggest decision
so far of the night.
- Oh, gosh, this is
a big decision.
- Missy Silverman,
deal or no deal?
- No deal.
[crowd shouting]
- I say, no deal!
No deal.
- Wow.
- Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe I did that.
That's so much money.
- It's a lot of money.
The question now is,
will your luck hold on?
One more case.
- Okay, one more case,
and I want the $5.
I want to see the $5.
Oh, girls.
Oh, all these numbers.
- You know, it's possible
that the $5
could be in this case, right?
Just as much of a chance.
- Oh. Oh!
[laughter]
Okay, let's go with 25!
- Summer.
- I don't even know.
I'm scared.
- Summer, anything.
She wants the $5,
but I would be happy
with anything
but the $300,000
or the $400,000.
One more time.
Hold onto that luck.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Summer, open the case.
- I can't look. I'm scared.
Please, low, low, five,
low, low, low, low, low,
I'm scared.
- Well, you're amazing.
I want my kids
to go to your preschool.
- Aww!
- Not just because
you're so kind and giving,
but also, I think
you're the only person
who could
run circles around them.
- Oh, thank you.
Give me a low number, please.
[laughs]
Please.
[all groaning]
[applause]
- Okay, before she calls,
I'm gonna tell you something.
You still have a one
out of four chance
of walking out of here
with $400,000.
If you decide to go further,
or you make an offer,
and she doesn't accept it,
and you're forced
to go further,
you have a three out of four
chance of opening
anything but the $400,000,
which will make the offer
after this one go up.
- Okay.
- So can you take the risk?
Do you feel lucky?
Do you want to make
a counteroffer?
We're about to get a call.
Let's see what this is.
- Oh, I'm so nervous.
- Yes, of course,
she's going to go down. Yeah.
- I'm so nervous.
- Hello.
Okay.
She said the safety net
is gone.
She said you're lucky,
but not that lucky.
- That's okay, that's okay.
I'm still feeling lucky.
- The offer dropped.
- I knew it would.
- The new offer is $84,000.
- Talk to your family.
- This is your counteroffer
time.
- Maybe now you counter.
- One case to open.
- How much?
- $95,000.
- I think $95,000.
- Okay, okay.
- You counter and you be happy.
- Okay.
I'm not really good at math.
- Missy Silverman,
deal or no deal?
- Well, I think I might
make a counteroffer, Howie.
- Okay, counter up.
And the offer is...
- $95,000.
[cheers and applause]
- $95,000, there's the offer.
- That's a lot of money.
That is a lot of money.
- Is the banker
going to take the $95,000,
or are you going to have to go
on and open one more case,
and if that happens,
is the $400,000
still gonna stay in play?
$95,000, $400,000.
Do we accept?
Is there risk?
Is she lucky?
You'll find out
when you come back.
♪ ♪
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
I had a heart problem.
I was told to begin my
Aspirin regimen,
and I just didn't listen.
Until I almost lost my life.
My doctors again ordered
me to take Aspirin,
and I do.
Be sure to talk to your doctor
before you begin an
Aspirin regimen.
Listen to the doctor.
Take it seriously.
People know Aflac...
Aflac!
...but not what they do.
So we're answering
their questions.
Aflac is auto insurance, right?
No.
Uh uh.
Is it homeowner's insurance?
No...
Uhuhuhuh!
Is it duck insurance?
Nope.
Ahhh!
Do they pay me money directly
when I get sick or injured?
Yeah.
Aflac!
You got it. You know Aflac!
Boom!
Get help with expenses health
insurance doesn't cover.
Get to know us at...
Aflac dot com.
Let's take a look at some
numbers:
4 out of 5 people who have a
stroke, their first symptom...
IS a stroke.
80 percent of all strokes and
heart disease? Preventable.
And 149 dollars is all it takes
to get screened
and help take control
of your health.
We're Life Line Screening...
and if you're over 50...
call THIS number, to schedule
an appointment...
for FIVE painless screenings
that go beyond
regular check-ups.
We use ultrasound technology to
literally look
INSIDE your arteries...
for plaque which builds up as
you age-
and increases your risk for
stroke
and cardiovascular disease.
And by getting them through this
package, you're saving over 50%.
So call today and consider these
numbers:
for just $149 you'll receive
five screenings
that could reveal what your body
ISN'T telling you.
I'm gonna tell you that was
the best $150
I ever spent in my life.
Life Line Screening. The Power
of Prevention.
Call now to learn more.
[dramatic music]
[cheers and applause]
- Wow, Missy Silverman
just made a counteroffer
of $95,000.
The banker's considering,
so she's deep in thought.
Very important decision,
because if she takes it,
you walk out of here
with $95,000
and a beautiful girls' trip.
You have the cruise
with Princess Cruises,
so you already have that,
so it's a win-win.
But if she says no
and doesn't take your offer,
the $95,000 comes off the table
and you have to open
another case.
If that one more case you open
is the $400,000,
the most you can leave with
is $50,000,
so it's a really
precarious time.
[phone ringing]
This is scary.
- I'm scared.
- I'm scared for you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[laughter]
- [sighs]
That's a lot of money.
- Right. Okay.
All right.
- Oh, what'd she say?
- She said
she's giving you a gift.
- Oh, that's nice.
She said that you've been
saying all game,
how lucky you are...
- Oh, God.
- And her gift to you...
is the opportunity to prove it.
It is no deal.
- Oh, my God!
- No!
- Oh!
- Play on.
- I'm good with that.
- You got this, you got it.
75% chance you're gonna win it.
- All right, Miss.
- Oh, I don't know.
- We were even just
second-guessing it,
so that's good.
- What case should I open?
[crowd shouting]
- I can tell you
what case not to open.
Do not open the $400,000 case.
- Oh, I hope
that doesn't happen.
- That is the landmine.
- Oh, gosh, all these numbers
mean stuff to me.
Oh, it's so hard.
8 is my birthday.
- Right.
- 13 is my son's birthday.
And then 7
is my dad's birthday.
Oh, my gosh,
I don't know what to do.
Okay, I'm gonna just say it.
- Say it.
- It's coming to me.
I'm praying it's a low number.
Number 7! Oh!
- Oh, my God.
- That's what I would pick.
I would have picked that.
- We're gonna pray,
we're gonna pray. I'm praying.
- This one case
can make you or break you.
- I hope it's make me.
[laughter]
- Jordana, anything,
anything but $400,000.
- So scary.
- Open the case.
- I'm not looking.
Please, low.
[cheers and applause]
Yay, yay!
That's good.
- That's great.
- That's good.
- That's awesome!
[cheers and applause]
- I'm so happy!
That's good.
That's pretty good.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh. Oh.
- Wow, look at that board now.
So you got three cases left.
One of them
is holding $400,000.
You believe it's this one?
- I don't know.
It could be.
[phone ringing]
Oh, no.
Oh, I'm freaking out.
Oh, Howie, banker,
friends, husband...
- Right.
- Kids, audience.
Hello, models.
- Okay.
- Oh, my gosh.
- All right.
- What'd she say?
Please, shaking.
- She said you pushed
your luck.
- Yes, you did.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh. Scary.
- You say it paid off.
- Yeah.
- They're saying it paid off.
Do you think it paid off?
- I don't--
I hope so, I hope so.
Oh, I hope so.
I hope it paid off.
- It did, it did.
- You would have walked out
of here with $95,000, right?
- If she took
that counter, yes.
- Yeah.
- She didn't.
- Would you walk out now
for $165,000?
- [exclaiming]
[cheers and applause]
[exclaiming]
- Yes!
- That's a lot of money.
Oh, my gosh.
That's a lot of money.
What do I do?
- Take it!
- Yes!
- Take it.
- Let me ask you.
[all chanting]
Take that deal!
- Deal?
[all chanting]
Take that deal!
- Let me ask you,
Missy Silverman,
deal or no deal?
[cheers and applause]
- Deal?
- Deal!
- Deal, deal, deal!
[cheers and applause]
Thank you, thank you,
oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Thank you! Thank you!
- Okay, come around here.
Okay, so congratulations.
You got $165,000,
you got a dream vacation, okay,
but we don't know
if you made a good deal.
- We don't.
- Had you said no deal
and you went one more time,
the next case you would
have opened would have been...
- Eight.
- Okay, Neka, open your case.
- Oh!
- Perfect timing.
You got out right
at the right time.
You had the $50,000 case.
Open your case.
Wow, Missy Silverman
is the lucky one.
Ran inf here
with $165,000,