Stay away
from those two cases.
- Okay, number 26!
- Michelle, open the case.
- Low, low, please,
please, please.
- You got the prize,
you got the prize!
- [cheering]
We're going away!
- By opening the case
that's holding
the Princess Cruises logo,
you have won a cruise
to one of Princess Cruises'
380 destinations
that span
over seven continents.
They are known to be the best
global premium cruise line.
Missy, discover the world
and relax at sea.
Congratulations.
You can go anywhere
with the girls.
You got the girls' trip.
- We're going on a cruise!
[cheers and applause]
Oh, my gosh. I'm so happy!
- Two more cases.
- Okay, two.
- Taylor.
- A little amount.
- Taylor, open your case.
- Oh, please.
- Small amount, left side.
- Little, left side, left side.
Yay! That's good.
Oh, that's good.
- That's great.
- Thank you.
- That's great, one more.
15!
- 15, that's Madi.
Madi, open your case.
- Oh, I can't look.
I'm nervous.
- So am I.
- Low, low, low, low.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
I'm freaking out.
- That's a great board.
- Oh, yay.
- You think you're
freaking out?
I think she's freaking out.
That's because the game
is going great for you,
not so great for her.
- Hello?
Hello?
- [whistles]
Wake up, banker!
- Whoa, whoa.
- Did she just do that?
- That was--hang on.
- Let's go, girl!
- What was that?
You scared me.
I didn't know what that--
did that come out of you?
[laughter]
How do you do that?
- Oh, boy.
Oh, my gosh.
- Right.
Okay. All right.
Okay, there's eight cases left
that have not been opened.
Two of them have huge amounts,
which means you have
a 25% chance
of walking out of here
with at least $300,000.
[cheers and applause]
You do,
if you continue to play on,
have to open up two cases,
so it's a little precarious,
but you're in good shape.
She understands
that you're in good shape.
She knows the board, and
that's why this next offer--
- Uh-huh.
- "Uh-huh."
- In good shape.
- $53,000,
and you still have
an opportunity to counteroffer.
- No, no.
- There's so much going on.
- No. No, no, no,
look at the board, okay?
You had a goal.
You're in a really
good position,
and that number
is not high enough.
- It's a high number, though.
- Don't take it.
- Honey?
- I think you should
keep going.
- Okay.
- Okay, well.
- So I'm gonna ask you
the question.
Missy Silverman,
deal or no deal?
[crowd shouting]
- Okay, Howie.
No deal!
- No deal.
Two cases to go.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Two cases to go.
Only two big amounts.
A little precarious,
but very exciting.
We'll find out what she picks
when you come back.
♪ ♪
- Hi!
announcer: There are only
eight cases left.
- Look at her board.
- Yeah.
- Look at that board.
- The question now is,
will your luck hold on?
announcer:
Has Missy gone too far?
- I'm scared.
I'm scared.
- I'm scared for you.
- I know.
announcer:
Or does she have the banker
right she wants her?
- Oh, it is about to get
real, young lady.
NAYSAYER SAID NO ONE
WOULD SUBSCRIBE TO A CAR
THE WAY THEY
SUBSCRIBE TO MOVIES.
WE DON'T FOLLOW THE NAYSAYERS.
♪ ♪ ♪
So Kim, you going for our big
Drive Safe & Save discount?
Yup, using the app. I've been
quite vigilant.
Sharon says step on it. The
meeting's started.
OK, write her back 'Dear Sharon,
don't mess with my discount!'
Faster Mommy, I gotta go to the
bathroom.
I do too honey, but we're gonna
hold it for Mommy's discount.
Easy, easy!
But you're in labor?
Don't mess with my discount!
Uh hem.
Get a discount up to 30%
with Drive Safe & Save
from State Farm.
I've got to tell you something.
With the Capital One
Venture card
you earn unlimited double miles
on every purchase, every day.
Not just airline purchases?
Everything.
Hey, how'd you get in here?
Cross-checking.
Nice.
What's in your wallet...
Oh, c'mon!
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM SAYS
YOU CAN'T MAKE A
400 HORSEPOWER SEDAN,
THAT'S ALSO
ENVIRONMENTALLY CONSCIOUS.
WE DON'T FOLLOW
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM.
♪ ♪ ♪
[dramatic music]c]
[cheers and applause]
- Welcome back
to "Deal or No Deal."
This is Missy Silverman.
Before the break,
you turned down $53,000.
You've won your dream trip.
- We've won our dream trip.
- Look at that board.
$300,000 and $400,000
are very good things.
- Yes.
- Even if you knock out
one of those big amounts,
the next offer's going down.
- Oh.
- Just stay away from those
two big amounts.
- Okay.
- Two cases to open.
- Case number 18!
- 18.
- I can't look.
I can't look.
- Elissa, open your case.
- Oh, please, please.
- Good.
- That's okay.
That's okay.
- It's really good.
- That's okay.
- One more case.
- Okay.
20! 20, 20.
- Amanza.
This is a very
important case.
If you can stay away from
the $300,000 and the $400,000,
you're looking
at a very big offer.
- Okay, I'm hoping, Howie.
- So, Amanza, just stay away
from those two amounts.
- Please, please.
- You have the best energy.
Just put some into this case
and it's gonna work.
- Oh, please, low, low, low...
[all chanting]
Low, low, low.
- Open the case.
- Low, low, low!
- Please!
- There you go.
- I'm scared.
[cheers and applause]
- That is good!
- That's good.
- Not only is that great--
if you decide to play on,
it's only one case at a time.
There are only six cases left.
You have a one
out of three chance
of walking out of here
with $300,000.
You still have not used
your counteroffer.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
- You're doing great.
- You are.
- You're doing really,
really great.
- Okay.
- Let's just hear it,
and we'll talk.
- She said you did
what you had to do.
- Yep, oh, yeah.
- I don't know what that means,
but yes,
I did what I had to do.
- So therefore, she has to do
what she has to do.
- Oh, boy. Okay.
Oh, well...
- How hard was it,
when you think back,
to turn down $53,000?
- It was very, very hard
to turn down $53,000.
- It was very hard.
- Yes.
- So if that was hard,
what are you gonna do...
- Oh, no.
- With $77,000?
- Oh!
- No.
- Look at her board.
- Yeah.
- Look at that board.
- That's a pretty board.
- And now, she only does one
at a time.
- Right.
- One at a time!
- It's not even time
for the counteroffer.
- Mom, then you can do
a counteroffer for the--
- What do you say?
- I'm saying she should wait
to counter-offer until, like,
if she knocks
one of the bigger ones.
- Yeah.
- She still can lose one.
She can still lose one of
the $300,000 or the $400,000.
- He doesn't always agree
with her, so he agreed.
- This is the first time
they have agreed?
- It might be.
The force is with you.
I'd keep going.
- But you realize,
if she knocks out
and loses one of those amounts,
either the $300,000
or the $400,000,
there's no safety net.
- Don't play it safe.
- He's saying,
your son just said,
"Don't play it safe."
- I know,
but it's a lot of money.
- You came to play.
- You know, you do a lot
for everybody else.
- I do.
- The question is,
what do you want to do
for yourself,
Missy Silverman?
Deal or no deal?
[crowd shouting]
[all chanting]
One more case! One more case!
- No deal!
One more case!
Oh!
Oh, my gosh, I'm scared,
but I feel lucky.
- Yes!
- Oh, I'm scared.
- One case.
- Okay, one case.
- Just keep your safety net
employed.
- Okay, 11!
11!
- Brittany.
- I'm so scared.
Oh, my gosh.
- Brittany, do what you can,
open the case.
- $5, $5!
- Low, low.
- I'm feeling the pressure.
- Oh, please, low, low.
Low, low, low, low, please.
Oh, that's good!
[cheers and applause]
- Wow!
Big offer coming your way
when we come back.
- Yes!
♪ ♪
- Oh, my gosh,
it's so exciting.
announcer: Whether it's
walking on the beautiful beach
at Universal's Volcano Bay...
- This is gonna be fun!
announcer: Or heading down
a water slide...
- Whoo!
announcer: Missy Silverman
never stops moving.
Internet that puts
you in charge.
Alright boys, time to eat.
That handles anything.
[ crowd cheering ]
That protects
what's important.
And reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
(MEG VO)
I can see if my endometriosis
pain gets better...
Or I can...
(SHERRY VO)
I can just suck it up...
Or I can...
(DIANE VO)
I can tell myself tomorrow
will be different...
Or I can talk to
my gynecologist today!
(AVO)
You didn't choose to have
endometriosis...
but you can choose to ask
if ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA is specifically
developed for women
with moderate to severe
endometriosis pain.
In clinical trials,
ORILISSA was proven to reduce 3
common types of
endometriosis pain,
painful periods,
pelvic pain in between
periods,
and pain with sex.
Don't use ORILISSA if you are or
may be pregnant,
have osteoporosis,
severe liver disease, or are
taking drugs like
cyclosporine or gemfibrozil.
It may cause abnormal
liver tests.
ORILISSA may change your
periods, making it hard
to know if you are pregnant.
It does not prevent pregnancy.
Use birth control that does not
contain hormones.
ORILISSA may cause suicidal
thoughts or actions.
It may also cause bone loss.
Ask your gynecologist if
ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA. Made for endo pain.
One-millionth order.
Millionth order.
♪
There goes our first big order.
44, 45, 46...
How many of these
did they order?
Ooh, that's hot.
♪
You know, we could sell these.
Nah.
♪
We don't bake.
Opportunity.
What we deliver by delivering.
[dramatic music]
[cheers and applause]
- All right, welcome back
to "Deal or No Deal."
Missy Silverman,
mom, wife, business woman,
won a dream vacation.
You've got a big offer coming.
You said, during the commercial
break, what did you say to me?
"It doesn't feel real?"
- It does not feel real.
- Oh, it is about
to get real, young lady.
[phone ringing]
[crowd jeering]
- Oh, the banker.
- Hello.
Okay.
You said it was hard
to turn down $53,000.
- It was.
- You said it was harder
to turn down $77,000.
- That's a lot of money.
- It is a lot of money.
- Oh, no.
- There's a new offer.
- What is it?
I can't take it.
- You have to make
a decision...
- Oh!
- About $117,000 dollars.
[cheers and applause]
- Wow.
- Oh, that's so much money.
- It just got serious
over there.
- It's serious.
- One case to open.
No counteroffer.
You have tears.
Why do you have tears?
Talk to me.
- Because she deserves this.
She is a beaming light,
and she deserves everything.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, honey.
- Oh, honey, I love you.
- I love you, honey.
- Oh, my gosh.
- So we discussed this.
You still have
your counteroffer.
- Right.
- You still have two
really big numbers up there.
- Yes, really big.
- Oh, yes.
- We may have reached
her goal a little bit.
[laughter]
Forget the $117,000, whatever.
Think about those numbers
up there.
- Forget the $117,000?
- For a second!
We're having a discussion.
- I can't forget that.
That's a lot of money.
- Think about
what the next five years
you have in store for you.
- Oh, that's a lot.
- That's a lot.
- I know.
- What's in store for you
in the five years? I don't--
- My kids are going to college,
and I don't want them to
come out with a lot of loans,
and that would really help.
- That would do more than help.
- Yes.
- You guys.
- What are you guys discussing?
- I say she keeps going.
- Keeps going. No counter.
You're saying no counter.
- Not yet. I think she saves
the counter until--
if she loses one of those.
- Keep going, keep going.
- It's exactly what he said.
- One more, one more.
- Oh, Howie.
- Here's the thing.
Right now, the only guarantee
you have is $117,000,
but you also have luck,
you have risk,
and you have $300,000
and $400,000
left in the game, so...
- Oh, gosh.
Oh.
- I'm gonna ask you.
Missy Silverman,
the biggest decision
so far of the night.
- Oh, gosh, this is
a big decision.
- Missy Silverman,
deal or no deal?
- No deal.
[crowd shouting]
- I say, no deal!
No deal.
- Wow.
- Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe I did that.
That's so much money.
- It's a lot of money.
The question now is,
will your luck hold on?
One more case.
- Okay, one more case,
and I want the $5.
I want to see the $5.
Oh, girls.
Oh, all these numbers.
- You know, it's possible
that the $5
could be in this case, right?
Just as much of a chance.
- Oh. Oh!
[laughter]
Okay, let's go with 25!
- Summer.
- I don't even know.
I'm scared.
- Summer, anything.
She wants the $5,
but I would be happy
with anything
but the $300,000
or the $400,000.
One more time.
Hold onto that luck.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Summer, open the case.
- I can't look. I'm scared.
Please, low, low, five,
low, low, low, low, low,
I'm scared.
- Well, you're amazing.
I want my kids
to go to your preschool.
- Aww!
- Not just because
you're so kind and giving,
but also, I think
you're the only person
who could
run circles around them.
- Oh, thank you.
Give me a low number, please.
[laughs]
Please.
[all groaning]
[applause]
- Okay, before she calls,
I'm gonna tell you something.
You still have a one
out of four chance
of walking out of here
with $400,000.
If you decide to go further,
or you make an offer,
and she doesn't accept it,
and you're forced
to go further,
you have a three out of four
chance of opening
anything but the $400,000,
which will make the offer
after this one go up.
- Okay.
- So can you take the risk?
Do you feel lucky?
Do you want to make
a counteroffer?
We're about to get a call.
Let's see what this is.
- Oh, I'm so nervous.
- Yes, of course,
she's going to go down. Yeah.
- I'm so nervous.
- Hello.
Okay.
She said the safety net
is gone.
She said you're lucky,
but not that lucky.
- That's okay, that's okay.
I'm still feeling lucky.
- The offer dropped.
- I knew it would.
- The new offer is $84,000.
- Talk to your family.
- This is your counteroffer
time.
- Maybe now you counter.
- One case to open.
- How much?
- $95,000.
- I think $95,000.
- Okay, okay.
- You counter and you be happy.
- Okay.
I'm not really good at math.
- Missy Silverman,
deal or no deal?
- Well, I think I might
make a counteroffer, Howie.
- Okay, counter up.
And the offer is...
- $95,000.
[cheers and applause]
- $95,000, there's the offer.
- That's a lot of money.
That is a lot of money.
- Is the banker
going to take the $95,000,
or are you going to have to go
on and open one more case,
and if that happens,
is the $400,000
still gonna stay in play?
$95,000, $400,000.
Do we accept?
Is there risk?
Is she lucky?
You'll find out
when you come back.
♪ ♪
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
I had a heart problem.
I was told to begin my
Aspirin regimen,
and I just didn't listen.
Until I almost lost my life.
My doctors again ordered
me to take Aspirin,
and I do.
Be sure to talk to your doctor
before you begin an
Aspirin regimen.
Listen to the doctor.
Take it seriously.
People know Aflac...
Aflac!
...but not what they do.
So we're answering
their questions.
Aflac is auto insurance, right?
No.
Uh uh.
Is it homeowner's insurance?
No...
Uhuhuhuh!
Is it duck insurance?
Nope.
Ahhh!
Do they pay me money directly
when I get sick or injured?
Yeah.
Aflac!
You got it. You know Aflac!
Boom!
Get help with expenses health
insurance doesn't cover.
Get to know us at...
Aflac dot com.
Let's take a look at some
numbers:
4 out of 5 people who have a
stroke, their first symptom...
IS a stroke.
80 percent of all strokes and
heart disease? Preventable.
And 149 dollars is all it takes
to get screened
and help take control
of your health.
We're Life Line Screening...
and if you're over 50...
call THIS number, to schedule
an appointment...
for FIVE painless screenings
that go beyond
regular check-ups.
We use ultrasound technology to
literally look
INSIDE your arteries...
for plaque which builds up as
you age-
and increases your risk for
stroke
and cardiovascular disease.
And by getting them through this
package, you're saving over 50%.
So call today and consider these
numbers:
for just $149 you'll receive
five screenings
that could reveal what your body
ISN'T telling you.
I'm gonna tell you that was
the best $150
I ever spent in my life.
Life Line Screening. The Power
of Prevention.
Call now to learn more.
[dramatic music]
[cheers and applause]
- Wow, Missy Silverman
just made a counteroffer
of $95,000.
The banker's considering,
so she's deep in thought.
Very important decision,
because if she takes it,
you walk out of here
with $95,000
and a beautiful girls' trip.
You have the cruise
with Princess Cruises,
so you already have that,
so it's a win-win.
But if she says no
and doesn't take your offer,
the $95,000 comes off the table
and you have to open
another case.
If that one more case you open
is the $400,000,
the most you can leave with
is $50,000,
so it's a really
precarious time.
[phone ringing]
This is scary.
- I'm scared.
- I'm scared for you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[laughter]
- [sighs]
That's a lot of money.
- Right. Okay.
All right.
- Oh, what'd she say?
- She said
she's giving you a gift.
- Oh, that's nice.
She said that you've been
saying all game,
how lucky you are...
- Oh, God.
- And her gift to you...
is the opportunity to prove it.
It is no deal.
- Oh, my God!
- No!
- Oh!
- Play on.
- I'm good with that.
- You got this, you got it.
75% chance you're gonna win it.
- All right, Miss.
- Oh, I don't know.
- We were even just
second-guessing it,
so that's good.
- What case should I open?
[crowd shouting]
- I can tell you
what case not to open.
Do not open the $400,000 case.
- Oh, I hope
that doesn't happen.
- That is the landmine.
- Oh, gosh, all these numbers
mean stuff to me.
Oh, it's so hard.
8 is my birthday.
- Right.
- 13 is my son's birthday.
And then 7
is my dad's birthday.
Oh, my gosh,
I don't know what to do.
Okay, I'm gonna just say it.
- Say it.
- It's coming to me.
I'm praying it's a low number.
Number 7! Oh!
- Oh, my God.
- That's what I would pick.
I would have picked that.
- We're gonna pray,
we're gonna pray. I'm praying.
- This one case
can make you or break you.
- I hope it's make me.
[laughter]
- Jordana, anything,
anything but $400,000.
- So scary.
- Open the case.
- I'm not looking.
Please, low.
[cheers and applause]
Yay, yay!
That's good.
- That's great.
- That's good.
- That's awesome!
[cheers and applause]
- I'm so happy!
That's good.
That's pretty good.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh. Oh.
- Wow, look at that board now.
So you got three cases left.
One of them
is holding $400,000.
You believe it's this one?
- I don't know.
It could be.
[phone ringing]
Oh, no.
Oh, I'm freaking out.
Oh, Howie, banker,
friends, husband...
- Right.
- Kids, audience.
Hello, models.
- Okay.
- Oh, my gosh.
- All right.
- What'd she say?
Please, shaking.
- She said you pushed
your luck.
- Yes, you did.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh. Scary.
- You say it paid off.
- Yeah.
- They're saying it paid off.
Do you think it paid off?
- I don't--
I hope so, I hope so.
Oh, I hope so.
I hope it paid off.
- It did, it did.
- You would have walked out
of here with $95,000, right?
- If she took
that counter, yes.
- Yeah.
- She didn't.
- Would you walk out now
for $165,000?
- [exclaiming]
[cheers and applause]
[exclaiming]
- Yes!
- That's a lot of money.
Oh, my gosh.
That's a lot of money.
What do I do?
- Take it!
- Yes!
- Take it.
- Let me ask you.
[all chanting]
Take that deal!
- Deal?
[all chanting]
Take that deal!
- Let me ask you,
Missy Silverman,
deal or no deal?
[cheers and applause]
- Deal?
- Deal!
- Deal, deal, deal!
[cheers and applause]
Thank you, thank you,
oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
Thank you! Thank you!
- Okay, come around here.
Okay, so congratulations.
You got $165,000,
you got a dream vacation, okay,
but we don't know
if you made a good deal.
- We don't.
- Had you said no deal
and you went one more time,
the next case you would
have opened would have been...
- Eight.
- Okay, Neka, open your case.
- Oh!
- Perfect timing.
You got out right
at the right time.
You had the $50,000 case.
Open your case.
Wow, Missy Silverman
is the lucky one.
Ran inf here
with $165,000,