- You did the perfect thing.
This is 400,000...
$100.
Your timing
was absolutely perfect!
How amazing is that?
Courtney Schlaud
shimmy and shaked her way
all the way
to $1/2 million.
Courtney Schlaud Day
has officially come to an end,
and so we have to say good-bye
for now.
I'm Howie Mandel,
and we'll see you right here
next time
on "Deal or No Deal."
male announcer:
Get ready for the fun,
the excitement,
and the adventure.
It's the game where
one of these 26 cases
holds the dream of a lifetime
at Universal Orlando Resort
on "Deal or No Deal."
Tony Oriente is ready to play.
- He is a husband.
He is a teacher.
He wants to be
a Golden Girl in Florida.
announcer: And tonight,
his heart
is set on winning a million.
- How amazing is that?
announcer: The banker
will be tough to beat.
- The banker wants to know,
do you have the guts?
- No deal!
announcer: But this just might
be Tony's big night.
- Are you looking
at that board?
- I'm looking at that board!
- The offers just went
to the next level.
- I see $1 million!
announcer: It's an emotional
ride like no other.
- Play the game. No deal.
- Call your friends.
Call your neighbors.
- Please don't be mad
at me for this. No deal!
announcer:
From Universal Orlando Resort,
it's a
one-of-a-kind thrill ride
filled with surprises
on "Deal or No Deal."
- Welcome to "Deal or No Deal."
Do you know that we have played
over 500 games on this show?
That's a lot.
All over the world too.
And no matter where we went,
you know what I learned?
It doesn't matter who you are.
Anyone can play this game,
and anyone can win $1 million.
But I'm the only person
who gets to do this.
Ladies, please.
[dynamic music]
♪ ♪
Wow.
Hello, ladies.
all: Hello, Howie.
- How are you? Okay. You ready?
These cases need opening,
and I just know the person
to do it: Tony Oriente.
How are you? How you doing?
- I am great.
- Good to meet you.
- [inaudible]. Thank you.
- Feel the love. How are you?
- Howie, I am fantastic.
I have been watching you
for so many years.
This is my all-time
favorite game show.
- Me too!
- You are my all-time
favorite game show host.
- Whoa!
- Yes!
- Well, thank you.
And you realize that this is
"Deal or No Deal."
I'm noticing bingo, but, uh...
- Yes. Actually, my favorite
pastime is playing bingo.
For many years
I was a bingo caller.
- Really?
- Yes.
So for fun,
can I pick my cases with this?
- You could do
whatever you want.
Tell me about you.
- I'm from Philadelphia,
Pennsylvania, originally.
Right now I live in the suburbs
of Philadelphia
with my husband
of four years, Dewey Oriente.
Love of my life.
And we have
three wonderful children.
- Really?
- We do. Yes.
- That's wonderful.
- We have Miss Sugar,
who is a beautiful
rag doll cat,
we have Coconut and Monroe,
which are 15-year-old
Bichons, and I know
that they're all watching.
Hi. Hi.
Hi.
- [laughs]
- Now that I've turned 50,
right now, I am back in school.
I've decided to get my degree
in elementary education.
- Wonderful. You ready to play?
- I'm ready to play, Howie.
- Oh, wow.
- Yes!
- Very good.
You're terrific.
I've only known you
for moments,
and you are probably
one of the most lovable people
I've ever met.
You really are...
- Thank you, Howie.
- And we want things
to happen for you.
Okay, so this is how we do it.
Each of the ladies are holding
a case from 1 to 26.
We know there's an amount
of money in each case,
packed there by a third party.
We don't know what case
is holding what amount.
The only thing we do know
is one of those cases
is holding $1 million.
[inaudible]
All you have to do is pick the
case that has a million in it.
- When I worked
at the bingo hall,
I met a very, very fond woman.
Her name is Jane.
I'm picking one of her
favorite lucky numbers.
We're going for case number 24.
- 24.
That's Kizzi.
Here you go.
- [inaudible].
- You feel the millions
in there?
- There's something in there.
- Well, that's...
- [giggling]
- It's something big.
I know that. Something big.
- All right.
- Yes.
- Well, hopefully
it's the biggest,
and the way we find out
is by opening those.
What's ever in those
is not in yours.
We're gonna start by opening up
six cases, Tony.
- Okay. Howie, did you ever
play bingo before?
- Many times.
- Many times?
- Yes.
- I'm no good at it, but I'm...
[laughing]
Our first number up--
if everybody
has their cards ready,
um...
We have number 5.
- Number 5 is Lani.
Open your case.
Small amount. That's okay.
- Yes! That's okay.
- That's good.
- That's good. Five more cases.
- Yes.
We're going no higher than that
the rest of these picks.
Here we go. The next number
we've picked was 17.
- 17. That's Ashley.
Open your case.
- Low, low, low,
low, low, low, low.
Yeah! [laughing]
Whoo!
- Four more.
This is my favorite game.
- Number 9.
- That's Patricia.
Open your case.
- Small, Patricia.
Small, small.
- That's okay. That's okay.
It really is, because you still
have six of the top
seven amounts still in play,
including $1 million.
- Yes!
- Three more.
- We have number 3.
- 3. Katie. Open the case.
- Yes!
- Oh, my God.
People who are just tuning in
are going, "What is this?"
- "What is going on?"
Number 1. Yes!
- Soraya. Open your case.
- Yeah!
Number 15.
- How about that? That's Madi.
- Hi, Madi.
- Open your case.
- Small. Small.
Ah!
- That was a good first round.
Six out of the seven top
amounts are still in play.
- Whoo!
- And I want
to tell you something.
You know, you sense it.
When somebody comes up here
and you talk to them,
you can sense what kind of vibe
they're giving out.
This audience loves you.
I would imagine, at home,
people are just going,
"Wow. This guy's amazing.
We want him to win money."
There's only one person--I will
tell you--there is one person
that it's not about
winning over,
and that is that lady
right there.
That lady wants you to leave
with as little as possible.
She wants to buy that case
from you right now
for as little as possible.
[phone ringing]
She's about to make
your first offer.
Hello?
She said she's having a little
trouble reading you, you know?
She said she can't tell.
She wants to know,
are you having a good time?
- [laughing]
Guys, are we all having
a good time? Yes!
- Good first round.
Great first offer:
$30,000.
Now, Tony,
it's "Deal or No Deal" 2.0.
There is one option.
Once in the game,
you can counter-offer.
If she accepts it,
she'll give you the money,
you give her the case,
and you go home.
If she says "no deal,"
you must play on.
Five cases to open.
So Tony...
- Yes.
- Oriente, deal or no deal?
all: No deal!
- Howie, $30,000 would get us
to our dream home,
which is our Golden Girls
house in Florida
that we really, really want.
But we'd also like
to add the lanai to it.
So for the first time,
I have to say: no deal.
- Close the box. Wow.
Top five amounts
are still in play,
from 300,000
all the way to a million.
We will open five cases
when you come back.
announcer: Tony's heart
is catching on.
- How amazing is that?
announcer: And the offers
are going up.
Will the banker take control?
- She's not happy.
announcer: Or can Tony
take it all?
- By popular demand, no deal!
- Wow.
Experience the style,
craftsmanship and technology
that have made the RX
the leading luxury
SUV of all time.
Lease the 2019 RX 350 for
$409 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
WITH THE CHASE MOBILE APP,
JASON WU COULD PAY PRACTICALLY
ANYONE, AT ANY BANK,
ALL WHILE PUTTING
ON A RUNWAY SHOW.
OR, HE CAN MAKE IT EVEN EASIER -
(MEOW)
WITH RECURRING PAYMENTS
TO HIS CAT SITTER.
AND NOW SHE'S READY
FOR THE CATWALK.
CHASE. MAKE MORE
OF WHAT'S YOURS.
Ready to get Positively Radiant?
Aveeno's sheer formula
packed with pure soy
evens tone and texture.
So skin looks like this.
And you feel like this.
Aveeno® Positively Radiant®
Get Skin Happy™
♪♪
Uh, uh.
[Karate sounds]
♪ Oh baby you ♪
♪ You got what I need ♪
♪ You got everything I need ♪
♪ Your love will never go away ♪
♪ 'Cause you ♪
♪ Oh you got what I need ♪
Amazon's got everything you need
and package tracking for all.
Welcome, everyone.
Each day Justin
chooses to walk.
At work...
And after work.
He does it all with
Dr. Scholl's.
Only Dr. Scholl's has
Massaging Gel Insoles
that provide
all-day comfort.
To keep him feeling
more energized.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to Move.
This is Ode
to State Farm
winning five
J.D. Power
awards in a row
for life insurance.
( ♪♪ )
In B minor.
Woman:
Great stuff.
So...
Your student loans are
holding you back...
from buying a house,
investing for retirement,
and living your best life?
It's time to refinance your
student loans with SoFi.
You could get a lower
monthly payment,
Amazing customer service,
And you can see your rate
in just 2 minutes.
Refinance your student loans,
and you could save big.
♪
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Welcome back to
"Deal or No Deal."
This is Tony Oriente.
He is a husband.
He is a teacher. He wants to be
a Golden Girl in Florida.
- [laughs]
- Should you walk out of here
with a million dollars,
what are the kind of things
you want to do, Tony?
- We are underwater in our
mortgage from the 2008...
- Bubble.
- The bubble that went off.
- Yes.
- And we've lost our home...
- Oh!
- And we're actually
in the process of moving
right now into a new place,
and it's okay, because it's
a new beginning for us.
- Right.
- So we're going to turn
this negative situation
into a positive thing
and just keep moving forward.
- All right.
Well, let's move forward.
We have five cases to open.
- Okay.
- Five cases.
[laughter]
Tony?
- Okay. I'm sorry about that.
- Yeah. Okay. All right.
- Number 4!
- That's Brenda.
Open your case.
- Whoo!
- All right. This is working.
- Lucky number 7.
- Number 7.
- Yes!
- Okay. That's Jordana.
Open the case.
That's not bad.
That's good.
This is working for you.
- This is working for me.
- Oh...
- I love it.
- Wow.
- We have a baker's dozen. 13.
- 13. Mahogany Lox.
Open your case.
- Yes!
Number 18.
- Okay. That's Elissa.
Open your case.
That's good. That's great.
One more case.
- Number 16.
- All right.
That's Jessica Lee.
Open your case.
Wow. You kept the top
five amounts in.
Look at that board.
You kept them all in.
How amazing is that?
All the huge numbers
are right there.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Okay. It's going great.
Going great.
- She's not happy.
- She said you keep this up,
you may become a platinum girl.
- [laughing]
$52,000.
Very real.
Tony, I can see--
I can see when I tell you
these numbers,
as much fun as we're having,
this means a lot to you.
You don't want
to do this alone.
- No.
- You brought supporters.
- I did.
- Can I meet them?
- Absolutely.
- All right.
- [laughing]
- Oh, my.
It's--I'm having déjà vu.
[laughter]
[stammering] Who are you?
- Hi, Howie. I am Dewey.
I am the husband.
- The husband.
Is this a coincidence?
- No.
It's in case we get separated,
we can say,
"Did you see somebody
that looks like me?"
- Aww!
Do you always--
[laughter]
You always
dress the same!
That's amazing.
all: Aww.
- That was our wedding picture.
- That's the wedding!
- That's the wedding.
- Yes.
- Oh, wow. Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- All right, so tell me
about Tony.
- Okay, so we just celebrated
our fourth anniversary.
I always believed
we are one person,
and then we were separated,
and we've spent our whole lives
looking for our heart and soul,
and that's him.
- Aww.
- Wonderful.
Hello.
- Hi, Howie.
- Who are you?
- I'm Rosemary, and I just
wanted to let you know
from the get-go
that we are all criers.
And...
- So I've seen.
- To prepare for today, Tony
gave us each our own hankie.
Our hearts are in this
no matter what happens today.
- Okay.
- Our hearts are in this.
- Wonderful.
You're here for Tony.
And who are you?
- Hi. My name is Nicole.
Tony has been my inspiration,
my best buddy.
He is so giving
and so selfless,
and I'm here to support you
as you win $1 million!
- All right.
So come over here, Tony.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Come over here.
So you could talk to them.
There's $52,000, guaranteed.
- Okay.
- There is an option
of a counteroffer,
which you can do,
or you could just say "no deal"
and go on and open up
four more cases,
so I'm gonna ask you,
Tony Oriente...
- Yes.
- Deal or no deal?
all: No deal!
- So I'm the Sophia of
the household--
of "The Golden Girls."
I have to ask Dorothy.
- Well, Ma, I think
you should--I think you should
continue to play this game.
I say no deal.
- By popular demand, no deal.
- No deal.
You just said "no" to $52,000.
What does that feel like?
- That's more than I would make
in a year.
That would help us so--that
would help us tremendously,
and I can't believe
I just put that back.
- It's okay.
[excited chatter]
- But you know what?
- [inaudible].
- Let's look forward.
Four cases to open.
- My next one, then, is...
- Okay.
- 19.
- Our anniversary.
- Okay. That's Natasha.
- Left.
- Low!
- Okay.
- Go left.
- Left.
- So remember, remember,
we want it to be a low number.
We want this streak
to continue.
The top five amounts are still
in play, including, you know...
- $1 million. Yes!
- $1 million.
We'll open more cases
when you come back.
announcer: The top five amounts
are still on the board.
- This is one of the best
boards she has ever seen.
announcer: And any one of them
can change Tony's life...
- I see $1 million!
Yes!
announcer: Forever.
- This is getting bigger.
It's getting better.
There is a feeling,
even backstage.
Everybody wants you to win.
NAYSAYER SAID NO ONE
WOULD SUBSCRIBE TO A CAR
THE WAY THEY
SUBSCRIBE TO MOVIES.
WE DON'T FOLLOW THE NAYSAYERS.
♪ ♪ ♪
I'm not hungry!
You're having one more bite
No!
One more bite!
♪
Kraft. For the win win.
[farmers bell]
(Driver)
Relax, it's just a bug.
That's not a bug,
that's not a bug!
(Burke)
Hit and Drone.
Seen it, covered it.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
(MEG VO)
I can see if my endometriosis
pain gets better...
Or I can...
(SHERRY VO)
I can just suck it up...
Or I can...
(DIANE VO)
I can tell myself tomorrow
will be different...
Or I can talk to
my gynecologist today!
(AVO)
You didn't choose to have
endometriosis...
but you can choose to ask
if ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA is specifically
developed for women
with moderate to severe
endometriosis pain.
In clinical trials,
ORILISSA was proven to reduce 3
common types of
endometriosis pain,
painful periods,
pelvic pain in between
periods,
and pain with sex.
Don't use ORILISSA if you are or
may be pregnant,
have osteoporosis,
severe liver disease, or are
taking drugs like
cyclosporine or gemfibrozil.
It may cause abnormal
liver tests.
ORILISSA may change your
periods, making it hard
to know if you are pregnant.
It does not prevent pregnancy.
Use birth control that does not
contain hormones.
ORILISSA may cause suicidal
thoughts or actions.
It may also cause bone loss.
Ask your gynecologist if
ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA. Made for endo pain.
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM SAYS
YOU CAN'T MAKE A
400 HORSEPOWER SEDAN,
THAT'S ALSO
ENVIRONMENTALLY CONSCIOUS.
WE DON'T FOLLOW
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM.
♪ ♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
- Wow. Welcome back to
"Deal or No Deal."
We are having quite a game
with quite a contestant,
one of the loveliest people
we have ever met on this show.
His name is Tony Oriente.
Tony, you are playing--you
have huge amounts on the board.
Life-changing amounts.
Before the break,
you chose case number 19.
- Yes. It's my anniversary,
July 19th,
so that's got
a very dear number to me.
- Wow.
- See, he's worth
a million dollars.
That case 19's only a penny.
- Yes.
- Yeah!
- I love the way you think.
- Penny! Penny! Penny!
- Natasha, open the case.
all: Penny! Penny! Penny!
- Tony, you are such a light.
It's an honor. It's an honor.
- Oh.
- It's okay.
- A big one.
- 400,000.
- It's good.
- It's okay. It's okay.
Top three amounts
are still in play.
- Number 6.
- 6!
- Number 6. That's Megan.
- Hi, Megan.
- Megan, open your case.
That's good!
- Okay. Good. Yes.
- That's really good.
- There you go, bud.
- All right!
- I'll take it.
[inaudible] amounts.
- All right. Two more.
- Two, two.
- Okay.
- Two more.
- Number 25.
- Okay.
- Number 25 is Summer.
Summer, open your case.
- Yeah!
- All right!
- One more. One more.
- One more.
- This is the last one
in this round.
- Well, we say in bingo,
"Eight, skate, and donate.
Who do we appreciate?"
Number 8!
- That's what we say.
That's what we say in bingo.
Neka, open your case.
both: Go! Go!
- [screams]
[all shouting]
- Are you looking
at that board?
- I'm looking at that board!
- What do you see
on that board?
- It's going this-a-way.
- Yeah.
- I see $1 million!
- Are you prepared to take
another phone call?
- Is it collect? I'm ready
for another phone call.
- Okay. Well, you can collect.
- Oh!
- Oh, my gosh.
- Oh.
- Oh, man.
- He's getting nervous.
- Well, that was a good round.
- Hello?
[tense music]
Okay.
♪ ♪
She does her homework,
you know?
And she's looking at the board,
and this is
one of the best boards
she has ever seen.
- Yeah!
- [inaudible].
Right now it's gonna be tough,
because this is real.
This is a guarantee.
This is...
$88,000.
- [chuckles nervously]
- He's gonna play the game.
- Honey!
[sighs heavily]
all: No deal!
- You know what to do.
Play the game. No deal.
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
- Ultimately, this is
a game of luck.
It really is. I mean,
it's luck versus risk...
- Yes.
- Versus timing.
But luck can change.
- It can.
- You know?
- It definitely can.
- You bought a house.
That's really lucky.
Own a home, to become
a homeowner, you were lucky.
You're in the home.
The market changed.
You're moving out
of that house.
Tony Oriente...
deal or no deal?
all: No deal!
- We've come this far, Tony.
- Don't do it.
- We've come this far, buddy.
- I have to open--
- [inaudible].
- If I have to open three more,
and I can see
that there are four
large amounts still there...
- That's right, baby!
That's it! That's it!
- Please don't be mad
at me for this. No deal!
- No deal.
Three cases.
- All right.
- Yes.
- Number 10.
- Vaeda.
- The left! The left!
- Left side or the top
of the right.
all: The left! To the left!
To the left!
- Can I please come hang out
with you
in that "Golden Girls" house?
- Any time. Yes.
- Oh!
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- All right. You have it.
- Oh, it's okay.
- You'll have money.
- All right.
- You still have three
huge amounts in play...
- Yes.
- From $300,000
to $3/4 million.
- Whoo! Yes! I'm ready.
- I am too.
- Okay.
- Pick another case.
- 22. Yes!
- 22. Anchal.
- Come on.
- Open your case.
A dollar. Dollar.
all: Ohhh.
[all groaning]
- All right.
We've still got the 50.
Still got the half.
- You hit two big amounts
in a row.
This is the last one.
There are two
big amounts in play.
Anything
but either of those two
would be really good for you.
- Number 12.
- Sarati. Open your case.
- We got this. We got this.
- Good luck charm.
all: Low! Low!
- Oh, yes!
- Yes! Yes!
- Wow. I'll tell you something.
Things just got
a little more dangerous.
We have a crucial offer
coming up.
What will he do?
We don't know. Come back.
It comes down to where
one case can tip a game.
announcer: Two huge amounts
are still in play.
- That's some serious money.
- Yes.
- Oh. No deal!
announcer: And one huge
surprise is on the way.
How do you gauge the
greatness of an SUV?
Is it to carry cargo...
or to carry on a legacy?
Its show of strength...
or its sign of intelligence?
In crossing harsh terrain...
or breaking new ground?
This is the Mercedes-Benz
SUV family.
If you've never seen
yourself in a Mercedes,
you've never seen these offers.
Lease the GLA 250
for just $379 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz
Spring Event.
Hurry in before April 30th.
One-millionth order.
Millionth order.
♪
There goes our first big order.
44, 45, 46...
How many of these
did they order?
Ooh, that's hot.
♪
You know, we could sell these.
Nah.
♪
We don't bake.
Opportunity.
What we deliver by delivering.
♪
With the Capital One Savor Card
you earn 4% cash back on dining
and 4% on entertainment.
So when you go out, you cash in.
What's In Your Wallet?
♪
What do you have there?
P3 It's meat, cheese and nuts.
I keep my protein interesting.
Oh yea, me too.
I have cheese and uh these
herbs.
P3 snacks.
The more interesting way to get
your protein.
[upbeat music]
- Okay. Welcome back to
"Deal or No Deal."
I'm standing with Tony Oriente,
a husband, a teacher,
one of the most fun contestants
we've ever had on this show.
You really are.
You want your future.
You want your dream home.
That was a tough round.
- That was a very tough round.
- Yeah.
- Still, when you look at it,
there's only eight cases
left in play.
You have a one-in-four chance
of walking out of here
with at least $1/2 million.
[phone ringing]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Hello?
Right. All right.
You knocked out a big amount.
- Yes.
- What do you think, Tony,
that did to your offer?
- I believe my offer went down.
[laughs] Down.
- The new offer is $69,000.
$69,000.
Talk to me for a second
what that would mean
in your life right now.
- That is the student
loans gone.
That is the down payment
on the house.
That is exactly
what I could use
to get the third length
of my life started.
- If you decide to go on, you
must open up two more cases.
- Okay.
- Talk about this.
- I think he's right.
I also think that I know
that he likes to take risks,
and I'm okay with that.
I believe there's magic
in that number 24 case.
- I'm trying to leave here
knowing a millionaire,
and since that moment
has passed,
I will settle for...
- A somewhat millionaire.
- 3/4 of one.
I say no deal and go for it.
- Okay. All right.
Tony Oriente...
Deal or no deal?
- Hmm.
[all shouting]
- Howie, when I look
at the board,
I have two cases
that I have to open.
I have a 50-50 chance
of hitting one of those
big amounts--
the 500 or the 750,000--
but that would leave me
still one of them in play.
I don't want to make
a counteroffer as of yet.
No deal.
- No deal. Close the box.
- No deal!
- Two cases to open.
Two cases to open.
- Yes.
- Scared?
- I'm very scared right now.
- I'm scared for you.
- Yes.
- All right.
Start picking a case.
- There's no cases here.
[laughter]
- I was wondering that myself.
- What happened?
- Where are they at?
- I don't know.
You know how to get
them out here.
- I do.
- What do you say?
- Ladies, please!
[dynamic music]
♪ ♪
- Yes!
- Oh, my gosh.
- Here's looking at you.
You know, it's amazing,
I got to say.
There is a feeling,
even backstage,
that you have energized.
Everybody is at the monitors.
Everybody wants you to win.
Everybody wants just to be
a part of it.
So let's keep that
positive energy going.
- Absolutely.
- Are you gonna keep going
with the bingo?
- I absolutely am.
- So you have two cases
to open.
- Yes.
- Pick a case.
- All right, Tony. You got it.
- Number 23.
- Okay. That's Anne Julia.
- Penny! Penny!
all: Penny! Penny! Penny!
- Left side. Open the case.
all: Penny! Penny!
- I wish you all
the best, Tony.
- Thank you.
- Good!
- That's good.
- [shouting]
- That's great. That's great.
- Thank you!
- One more.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Okay.
This is the last case
to open in this round.
What is that case number?
- It's my birthday: 20.
- 20!
- That's Amanza.
This is a crucial case.
It is time to see
what is in Amanza's case.
Is it gonna be positive?
Is it gonna be negative?
We cannot break that net.
We need the penny.
Amanza, it is up to you.
- I want to say I know
how scary it is
to go through change
and to kind of start over.
I just recently went through
something like that myself.
The day I moved
into my new apartment,
I found out that
"Deal or No Deal"
was coming back,
and I got on the show,
and it changed my life,
and I think it's about
to change yours.
- Open your case.
all: Penny. Penny! Penny!
- Here I go.
all: Penny! Penny! Penny!
Penny! Penny!
[all screaming]
- Oh, wow.
This is getting bigger.
It's getting better.
Huge money in.
You are about
to get a huge offer.
You're very emotional.
So is everybody.
You don't want to miss this.
Call your friends.
Call your neighbors.
"Turn on CNBC right now."
- Wait, guys. Stop, stop, stop.
Check it out.
Right over there.
One donut. That's it.
Just one donut. Come on.
announcer: For Tony,
a Voodoo Doughnuts offer
is an automatic deal.
- These are the best donuts
that I ever had.
Universal next. Come on, guys.
♪♪
Every day,
visionaries are creating
the future.
♪♪
So, every day,
we put our latest technology
and unrivaled network to work.
♪♪
The United States
Postal Service makes
more e-commerce
deliveries to homes
than anyone else
in the country.
♪♪
Because the future only
happens with people
who really know how
to deliver it.
Because the future only
happens with people
WITH THE CHASE MOBILE APP,
JASON WU COULD PAY PRACTICALLY
ANYONE, AT ANY BANK,
ALL WHILE PUTTING
ON A RUNWAY SHOW.
OR, HE CAN MAKE IT EVEN EASIER -
(MEOW)
WITH RECURRING PAYMENTS
TO HIS CAT SITTER.
AND NOW SHE'S READY
FOR THE CATWALK.
CHASE. MAKE MORE
OF WHAT'S YOURS.
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
So, I needed legal advice,
and I heard that my cousin's
wife's sister's husband
was a lawyer, so I called him.
But he never called me back!
If your cousin's wife's sister's
husband isn't a lawyer,
call LegalZoom and we'll
connect you with an attorney.
LegalZoom.
Where life meets legal.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Tony Oriente just said
it to me.
I'm gonna say it to you.
Wow. This is a husband.
This is a teacher.
He's about to get a big offer.
That board is amazing.
Two huge amounts
still remain in play.
We're about
to get an offer, and...
- Ooh.
- We're at the part of the game
where if you continue to go on,
it is one case at a time.
- [chuckles nervously]
Hello?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Last time,
you had a one-in-four chance
of walking out of here
with at least
$1/2 million, right?
- Yes.
- I told you that last time.
- And now,
you have a one-in-three chance
of walking out of here
with 1/2 million.
The offers just went
to the next level.
Six figures.
$136,000.
- [chortling]
- I have two words: safety net.
Safety net. No deal.
- You can also counter-offer.
- Yes.
- If she says "no deal,"
the money's off the table,
and you still open
one more case.
Tony Oriente, deal or no deal?
all: No deal!
- No deal!
- Wow.
- All right. All right.
All right. All right.
All right.
- I just turned down $136,000!
- Spin the ball!
- Do it! Do it!
- Do it!
- Do it, baby!
- Spin it!
- You know why you did that?
You know why you did that?
- Spin it!
- For a chance to make
your dream come true.
- Yes.
- It's tough.
- It is tough.
- But good things
are hard to get.
You work hard,
and it's a lot sweeter.
- Just four.
- One case to open.
- Let's do this.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Number 2.
- Okay. Taylor.
You saw Tony's tears.
You saw Tony's angst.
Because Tony knows,
more than anybody in this room,
one case can either skyrocket
the next offer...
or cut the safety net.
This case is more important
than any other case
up until this time in the game.
Taylor, let's find that dollar.
Open the case.
- Find that dollar.
- Tony, just in the short time
that I've known you,
you are one of the most
deserving and humble people
that I've met,
and we're all here
with you right now,
and there's nothing that
I'd rather do
than open up
a low number right now.
- Come on.
all: Penny! Penny! Penny!
Penny! Penny!
Penny! Penny! Penny!
- Aw.
- It's okay.
- That's okay.
- Okay.
- That was a big hit,
'cause now there is
no longer a safety net.
In order to find out
if this has the $1/2 million,
you're going to have to
continue to turn down offers,
and you're gonna have
to go all the way.
Does it have the 1/2 million?
Is it worth waiting for?
We're all gonna have
to find out
if that $1/2 million is there.
Wait. We're going to break,
and we'll be back
with more "Deal or No Deal"
when you return.
[farmers bell]
(Driver)
Relax, it's just a bug.
That's not a bug,
that's not a bug!
(Burke)
Hit and Drone.
Seen it, covered it.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
There's little rest
for a single dad,
and back pain made it hard to
sleep and get up on time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid,
plus the 12 hour pain
relieving strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a Better AM.
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
Incomparable design
makes it beautiful.
State of the art technology
makes it brilliant.
The visionary Lexus NX.
Lease the 2019 NX 300 for
$359 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
I'm not hungry!
You're having one more bite
No!
One more bite!
♪
Kraft. For the win win.
I have a vision
correction number,
But I'm more than a number.
When I'm not teaching,
I'm taking steep grades
and tight corners.
My Essilor lenses offer more
than vision correction
with three innovative
technologies
For my ultimate in vision
Clarity
And Protection
Together in a single lens:
The Essilor Ultimate
Lens Package.
So, I can do more
of what I love!
Buy two pairs of
Essilor's best lenses
and get a $100 back instantly.
See more. Do more. Essilor
[upbeat music]
- Welcome back to
"Deal or No Deal."
Tony Oriente is looking
for his Golden Girl home,
which is still possible.
There's an offer coming up.
In the last round, the
biggest amount was knocked out.
There is still $1/2 million
on the board.
One case to open at a time.
- Okay.
- Odds are you'll open
smaller amounts.
How are you feeling?
- I need a little recharge
right now, Howie,
so I have a favor to ask.
- Go ahead.
- I'd like to go up there
and hang with the pretty girls
just for a moment
and hang with the models
so we can all share our outfit.
- Let's do it.
- Can my husband join me too?
- Go ahead.
- Go, go, go.
- Aww, hi.
- Whoo-hoo!
- [laughs] You guys remind me
of the Care Bears.
[laughter]
- They do.
- Ooh!
- Uh-oh.
- Okay. Hello?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Right. Right.
I know.
She said you're lovely,
but this is business.
- Ooh. Ooh! Okay.
- All right. It dropped.
- Yes.
- Significantly.
- Ooh.
- Almost in half. $71,000.
$71,000 is a lot of money.
One case to open.
You have a
four-out-of-five chance
of opening anything
but the 1/2 million,
but if you hit the 1/2 million,
the most you can go home
with is 50,000.
The banker wants to know,
do you have the guts?
Do you have the guts to go on?
- Yes, he has the guts.
Sorry, honey. You are certainly
no match for my husband.
- That's right. Yes!
- That being said,
$71,000 is a lot of money.
What are you telling him to do?
- I think now it's time
for the counteroffer.
- So you realize you have to
make a counter
that is reasonable.
- Yes.
- Because she, like yourself,
is just looking at the boards.
She is looking at the odds.
Tony Oriente, deal or no deal?
all: No deal!
- Banker, there's five cases
left up there.
If you averaged out five cases,
it would be $100,000
is the average for all of it,
and I would like to make
a counteroffer for $100,000.
- Up until now, the game
has totally been in your hands.
- Yes.
- And now you have just handed
control over to the banker.
It is up to her
to listen to your reasoning.
The decision is all hers.
The game is yours.
[phone ringing]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Are you ready
to hear the answer?
- I'm ready.
- Hello?
♪ ♪
Okay. All right. She said
that's a very close call.
Based on emotion,
that's a good offer, right?
- Yes.
- That's what she said.
This is not about emotion.
This is about business.
- This is business.
- She says no deal.
all: Awww.
- It's all right.
- All right.
- Okay.
- It's all right.
- It's okay, baby.
- One case.
We're gonna do this.
- We're gonna do it.
- Baby, come on, come on...
- Number 21.
- Malika.
All right. Let it be a dollar.
Let it be a penny.
Anything but the $1/2 million.
Let's feel it.
Open the case.
Come on.
[all groan]
- It's all good.
It's all good.
- All good.
- You know, this game plays
a big psychological game.
- Yes.
- When you see big amounts,
huge amounts of money
don't matter to people anymore,
but the truth is, you have
a one-out-of-four chance
of walking out of here
with $50,000.
- Yes!
- 50,000. Hello?
Okay. Way down,
but still a lot of money.
- Okay.
- $10,000.
$10,000 is a guarantee.
One case to open.
Tony Oriente, deal or no deal?
- No deal. No deal.
- Might as well play it out.
- No deal!
- Oh, my gosh.
One case to open.
- 11!
- All right.
Brittany, open the case.
- Low! Oh!
- It's okay. It's okay.
[phone ringing]
- Hello? Okay.
- Oh.
- $40.
Tony Oriente, deal or no deal?
- No deal!
- No deal.
- Pick a case.
Oh, my gosh.
- 26!
- Michelle, open your case.
- Yes!
- The final offer.
The final offer is--okay.
All right. $70.
Tony Oriente, deal or no deal?
- Ehh.
- Deal!
- Deal. You're taking $70.
Her case had the penny!
The penny was there.
Open your case.
Tony Oriente could not find
the end of the rainbow