AND THERE'S QUITE A NUMBER OF
EARNINGS THIS MORNING AND YOU
CAN SEE THAT IN THE S&P AS WELL.
IT'S LEADING EVERYTHING HIGHER
THE INDUSTRIAL NAMES LIKE THAT
ARE ALL BETTER THAN EXPECTED
BUT QUITE THE HOUR
WHAT IS THE TAKE FROM THE NASDAQ
RIGHT NOW?
>> MORGAN, THIS IS JUST THE
FIRST FEW MINUTES.
NOT EVEN AN HOUR
REMEMBER HOW PEOPLE WERE TALKING
ABOUT THAT OTHER IPO THREE WEEKS
AGO JUST MINUTES IN, IT'S A LONG
JOURNEY.
THE COMPANIES SEEM TO KNOW THAT.
THEY SAY THE OUTLOOK IS FOR
INVESTORS AND WE TRY TO KEEP
THEM EDUCATED.
GUYS
>> JOHN, GREAT WORK.
FASCINATING DAY AS WE CONTINUE
TO WATCH THE SESSION
WE WILL SEE WHAT HAPPENS THIS
AFTERNOON.
LET'S GET OVER TO "THE HALF" AT
HG.
>> CARL, THANKS.
I'M SCOTT WAPNER
WELCOME TO "THE HALFTIME
REPORT."
OUR BREAKING NEWS, TWO SURGING
IPOs, MUELLER REPORT RELEASED IN
THE PAST HOUR.
AND BIG WELL-KNOWN MARKET
WATCHER SAY STOCKS COULD BE
PRIME FOR A SHORT-LIVED PULLBACK
BECAUSE OF WEAKNESS IN A SECTOR
THAT COULD CAUSE A LOT OF MONEY
TO ROTATE OUT OF IT.
WELCOME, WE WILL DISCUSS ALL OF
THAT WITH OUR INVESTMENT
COMMITTEE TODAY, MANY JOSH
BROWN, STEVE WHITE, OUR CHIEF
EQUITY STRATEGIST, AND COURTNEY
GIBSON, THE PRESIDENT OF LUKE
CAPITAL.
LET'S BEGIN WITH THE MARKETS
PINTEREST AND ZOOM SURGING
THOSE STOCKS OPENING FOR
TRADING.
WE'RE ALSO ON RECORD WATCH
S&P INCHING CLOSER TO ITS NEW
HIGHS.
THE QUESTION IS STEVE WEISS,
WILL WE GET THERE?
AND THEN WHAT?
>> SO LOOK, EARNINGS HAVE BEEN
PRETTY DECENT --
>> MAYBE BETTER THAN THE WORST
FEARS OF TWO WEEKS AGO.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WHAT'S IMPORTANT IS WE ARE
SEEING IT IN COMPANIES THIS
RELATE DIRECTLY TO THE ECONOMY
THAT ARE SAYING BASICALLY THE
ECONOMY ISN'T AS BAD AS WE
THOUGHT.
THERE'S NOWHERE ELSE TO GO
I THINK IT WOULD BE A NONEVENT
WE'RE SEEING A HEALTHY IPO
MARKET LIFT ASIDE.
SO EVERYTHING IS IN THERE TO
DRIVE THE MARKET HIGHER,
PARTICULARLY WITH RATES STILL
STAYING LOW EVEN THOUGH THE
TEN-YEAR MOVED UP.
TO ME IT'S WHERE YOU PUT YOUR
MONEY, WHERE YOUR CAPITAL GOES,
INTO WA SECTORS AND SPECIFICALLY
INTO WHAT STOCKS
THAT'S WHERE YOU GOT TO BE
CAREFUL.
WE ARE SEEING A BIG ROTATION WE
WILL TALK ABOUT LATER, HEALTH
CARE, A LOT OF HEALTH CARE, AS
WE HAVE BERNIE SANDERS, HEALTH
CARE FOR ALL, THAT WILL PRESSURE
HEALTH CARE.
BUT I THINK THAT'S THE
OPPORTUNITY.
THAT'S NEVER COME THROUGH WITH
HILLARY CLINTON BEFORE, AND
THAT'S WHERE WE ARE.
>> DOW'S UP BETTER THAN 100.
40 POINTS AWAY, LITTLE LESS THAN
THAT, FOR A NEW HIGH ON THE S&P.
>> RIGHT NOW I THINK THE MARKET
IS AN INTERESTING PLACE.
WE'VE SEEN THE LAST SEVERAL
YEARS ALL OF THE MONEY FLOWING
INTO INDEX FUNDS, AND I THINK
THAT'S OKAY.
THERE'S A PLACE FOR THAT INNER
PORTFOLIO.
BUT IF THERE EVER WAS A TIME FOR
ACTIVE MANAGERS TO SHINE, THIS
IS IT.
WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT ROTATING OUT
OF HEALTH CARE, MOST OF OUR
CLIENTS DON'T ROTATE OUT OF
SECTORS THEY WILL OVERWEIGHT OR
UNDERWEIGHT AND WHAT STOCKS
YOU'RE PICKING IN THOSE SPACES
THAT WILL OUTPERFORM IN THE
MARKET WE SEE GOING FORWARD.
I THINK THE ECONOMY IS DOING
WELL
I'VE SAT ON THIS PANEL AND HEARD
PEOPLE TELL ME IT'S DOOMSDAY BUT
WE CONTINUE TO SEE THE
RESILIENCE OF THIS MARKET AND
RESILIENCE IN THE CONSUMER THAT
CONTINUES TO ALLOW THIS MARKET
TO RISE.
MAYBE IT DOESN'T GO AS HIGH
AS -- OR WE'RE NOT SEEING THE
RISE IN RATE AS MUCH AS WE SAW
IN 2018 BUT WE'RE GOING TO
CONTINUE TO SLOWLY TICK HIGHER
UNLESS WE SEE SOME CATASTROPHIC
THINGS HAPPEN IN THE MARKETPLACE
RIGHT NOW.
>> JOSH, YOU WANT TO TAKE AIM AT
THE IPOs, WHICH BOTH ARE SURGING
OFF THE OPEN, PINTEREST AND
ZOOM
>> I THINK IT'S GREAT YOU CAN DO
IPOs
I THINK IT'S GREAT PEOPLEON TH
STREET ARE TALKING ABOUT IPOs.
THERE'S A LOT OF INVESTOR
ENTHUSIASM
I HAVE BEEN RETICENT TO GET
INVOLVED
I DID NOT LIKE LYFT, AND I WAS
PRETTY CLEAR ABOUT WHY
I PROBABLY WON'T GET INVOLVED IN
EITHER OF THESE TWO.
BUT I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT THAT
WHEN YOU LOOK AT WHAT'S
HAPPENING WITH UNDERWRITINGS IN
GENERAL AND YOU SAY TO YOURSELF,
WHERE ARE ALL OF THESE DEALS
OCCUR, THEY'RE NOT ONLY TECH
WE HAPPEN TO BE TALKING ABOUT
TWO TECH NAMES TODAY BUT LEVI'S
WAS A HUGE DEAL, VERY BIG DEAL
THE AVERAGE IPO THIS YEAR IS UP
20% FROM WHERE IT WAS OFFERED,
WHICH IS PHENOMENAL.
LYFT OBVIOUSLY PULLS THAT
AVERAGE DOWN
THE AVERAGE TECH IPO, THOUGH, IS
UP 34%
YEAH, A LOT OF ENTHUSIASM.
BY THE WAY, I DO THINK THAT
THERE'S A COROLLARY TO WHAT'S
HAPPENING WITH HEALTH CARE
VERSUS TECH RIGHT NOW TO WHAT WE
SAW 20 YEARS AGO
THE LAST TIME YOU SAW THE HEALTH
CARE SECTOR TRAIL THE OVERALL
MARKET BY 17% POINTS, WHICH IS A
HUGE DIFFERENTIAL, WAS IN THE
LATE '90s.
WHAT WAS GOING ON BACK THEN?
PEOPLE WERE ONLY INTERESTED IN
GROWTH COMPANIES, WOULD NOT BUY
ANYTHING ELSE.
BUFFETT DIDN'T KNOW WHAT HE WAS
DOING ANYMORE SUDDENLY
YOU SAW HEALTH CARE STOCKS
COMPLETELY NEGLECTED, LEFT BY
THE WAYSIDE.
I THINK YOU'RE SEEING A LITTLE
ECHO OF THAT
LET'S KEEP AN EYE ON IT.
IF EVERYONE ONLY WANTS GROWTH,
THAT DOES CREATE OPPORTUNITIES
FOR PEOPLE LIVING TO LOOK AT
DRUG DISCOVERY COMPANIES LIKE
BIOTECH.
>> SO KATE MOORE, DOES BETTER
ECONOMIC DATA THAN EXPECTED AS
STEVE WEISS SAID, EARNINGS
BETTER THAN APRINTICIPATED A FEW
WEEKS AGO, IS THAT A LICENSE TO
BUY STOCKS
A NEW RETAIL NUMBER TODAY, BEST
RETAIL NUMBERS SINCE '17.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
LABOR MARKET IS IN GOOD SHAPE.
WE HAVE A LOT OF GOOD MACRODATA
SUPPORTING A SLOW BUT EXPANDING
GLOBAL ECONOMY
THE FIRST THING I'M WATCHING IS
THE EARNINGS REVISION.
THIS HAS BEEN AWFUL THE LAST
FOUR MONTHS.
DOWNWARD DIVISIONS RELATIVE TO
UPWARD DIVISIONS TRAILED OUT
THAT SEEMS TO BE BOTTOMING OUT
WE'RE WATCHING THAT CLOSELY.
I WOULD NO HEALTH CARE HAD THE
BEST EARNINGS DIVISION RATIO IN
THE U.S.
SO THIS IS A DISCONNECT TWIN THE
FUNDAMENTALS AND FEAR OF WHAT
MAY HAPPEN WITHIN CHANGE OF
POLICY
THE OTHER THING I'M WATCHING
CLOSELY IS FUND FLOWS.
WE'VE SEEN HUGE AMOUNT OF
REDEMPTIONS FROM EQUITY FUND
FLOWS TODAY.
WE KEEP TALKING ABOUT THIS BUT
WHEN YOU ANNIZE THIS DATA BOTH
AS A PERCENTAGE OF ASSETS UNDER
MANAGEMENT AND ASSET OF TERMS,
THESE ARE PHENOMENALLY LARGE
NUMBERS.
I DON'T THINK PEOPLE ARE EXCITED
ABOUT THIS RALLY
I THINK THE TRADE IS HIGHER IN
THE NEAR TERM EVEN THOUGH WE
WILL HAVE MORE VOLATILITY
THROUGHOUT THE SECOND QUARTER.
>> LET ME ASK YOU, I HATE TO ASK
YOU THIS WAY, BUT DO YOU AGREE
WITH LARRY FINK --
>> ANSWER YES, ANSWER YES.
>> DOES THAT POINT OF VIEW THAT
HE PUT FORTH SOUND REASONABLE
THAT YOU HAVE HAD ALL OF THIS
MONEY SITTING ON THE SIDELINES,
YOU'VE HAD SOME WITHDRAWALS AND
YOU'RE GOING TO GET THIS MONEY
COMING BACK INTO THE MARKET FOR
MANY OF THE REASONS WE DISCUSSED
HERE AND THAT WILL CARRY YOU TO
NEW HIGHS AND BEYOND THAT WHAT
HE CALLED A MARKET MELTDOWN?
>> WELCOME, I HAVE HUGE SFREKT
FOR LARRY NOT JUST AS MY LEADER
BUT ALSO A THINKER
HERE'S WHAT I WOULD SAY, I THINK
HE'S RIGHT THAT THERE'S A LOT OF
MONEY ON THE SIDELINES AND
THERE'S POTENTIAL.
WHAT I WORRY ABOUT IS WE DON'T
HAVE A CATALYST AND IN THE VERY
NEAR TERM, OVER THE NEXT FEW
QUARTERS, IF WE FAIL TO HAVE
STABILITY AND IN FACT UPGRADES,
GROWTH DATA LOOKS OKAY, WE GET
THROUGH TRADE STOCK, FED STAYS
ON HOLD, I THINK THAT MONEY HAS
TO COME BACK INTO THE MARKET
I THINK THAT WILL LEAD TO A
SUPPORT.
I THINK WE HAVE TO WATCH
CLOSELY.
I THINK TECHNICALS SHOULD BE A
BIG PART OF EVERYONE'S PLAYBOOK.
>> WHERE WILL THE CASH GO COMING
OUT OF THE MARKET?
>> THERE'S SO MUCH MONEY FLOWING
INTO FIXED INCOME.
WE HAVE SEEN IT ON INSTITUTIONAL
INVESTORS, LIKE INDUSTRY WIDE
BECAUSE WE TRACK FROM A NUMBER
OF DIFFERENT SOURCES.
>> THAT WAS PART OF LARRY'S
POINT.
>> YES
THE MONEY IS GOING INTO FEARS
WE'RE ENTERING INTO A SLOWER
GROWTH PERIOD, REPRICING OF FED
EXPECTATIONS.
>> BUT THOSE ARE DATED NUMBERS
TOO.
NOW WE'RE SEEING CREDIT STARRED
TO BE FUELED BY THE TEN-YEAR,
START TO SELL A LITTLE BIT,
RIGHT?
>> I'M JUST TALKING ABOUT THE
SLOW FUND DAYS WE HAD LAST WEEK
SHOWING A SLOW ENTHUSIASM FOR
BONDS.
WE KNOW THERE ARE PLACES FOR
BONDS IN THE PORTFOLIO CYCLE BUT
THAT SAID, THE EQUITY BETWEEN
BONDS AND FLOWS IS SOMETHING TO
WATCH.
>> I DON'T AGREE PUTTING MONEY
INTO BONDS -- I AGREE PUTTING
MONEY INTO BONDS, I DISAGREE
ABOUT THE DATA OR WHAT IT MEANS
BEHIND IT.
MY INDUSTRY WHERE EVERY DOLLAR
IS GOING IS THE R.A. CHANNEL
THEY USE IT TO TWO WAYS,
TACTICALLY OR PHYSICALLY
WHEN THEY USE IT TACTICALLY
THERE'S A SIGNAL TECHNICALLY OR
SOME KIND OF TRIP WIRE THAT'S
CAUSED THEM IN A RULES-BASE ADD
APPROACH TO MOVE MONEY OUT OF
EQUITIES AND TEMPORARILY THAT
MONEY DOES GO INTO FIXED INCOME
SLEEVES IN A PORTFOLIO THAT COST
NOTHING IN TERMS OF INTERNAL
SCENARIO, FREE BASIS POINTS, BUT
IT'S NOT THERE BECAUSE THE
PERSON DIRECTING IT -- I'M
TALKING ABOUT BILLIONS OF
DOLLARS, NOT A FEW MILLION --
THE PERSON DIRECTING IT DOES NOT
WANT TO SIT IN CASH.
IN MY BUSINESS IF YOU SIT IN
CASH, THE CLIENT TAKES CASH.
>> I BUT IT'S NOT --
>> I WANT TO FINISH THIS
THOUGHT.
IT'S NOT AN EXPRESSION OF WHAT
THE PERSON THINKS OF THE ECONOMY
BUT A PERSONAL MANAGEMENT TOOL
LEADING A LITTLE BIT OF RISK
WITH THE OPPORTUNITY TO GO BACK
INTO EQUITIES.
WE'VE SEEN THAT OVER AND OVER
AGAIN.
>> YOU MAY BE CORRECT FOR A
CERTAIN SEGMENT OF IT BUT YOU
CAN'T SUGGEST WHAT KATE IS
SUGGESTING, THE DATA SHE SEES IN
THE FUND FLOW SUGGESTS
THERE WAS A SCARE ABOUT THE
ECONOMY.
>> THIS YEAR
THIS YEAR.
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT 2019.
WE'VE DONE GREAT SURVEYS OF OUR
INSTITUTIONAL CLIENTS.
WE'VE SEEN PENSION FUNDS AND
ALLOCATORS TALK ABOUT SHIFTING
THEIR MONEY OVER A LONG TERM OUT
OF EQUITIES AND INTO FIXED
INCOMES AND INTO ALTERNATIVES.
THE LATTER PART IS WHERE I'M
SIGHING A TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF
FLOWS.
>> WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT TAKING IT
OUT OF PUBLIC EQUITIES AND GOING
INTO THE PRIVATE MARKETS, THAT'S
EXACTLY WHERE WE ARE SEEING A
TON OF ASSETS FLOWING.
THE RPs, IF YOU LOOK AT THE
SEARCHES OUT THERE BY THE LARGE
INSTITUTIONALCONSULTANTS,
THEY'RE MOVING MONEY.
>> HERE'S MY IMPRESSION ON YOUR
VIEW WHY IT'S HAPPENING, I JUST
DON'T BELIEVE AND THE PEOPLE
THAT I KNOW WHO INVEST IN
I.R.A.s ARE GOING TO SELL
POSITIONS, PAY TAXES AND HIEDE
FIXED INCOME.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT THE BOTTOM LINE
IS, I WANT TO WRAP THAT UP, IT
DOESN'T MATTER WHY IT HAPPENED
THE POINT IS THAT IT HAPPENED.
>> YES, IT DOES MATTER.
>> AND LARRY FINK SUGGESTS IN
PART BECAUSE IT HAS HAPPENED AND
PEOPLE HAVE MISSED, THEY GOT
OVERLY SCARED ABOUT PERHAPS WHAT
WAS GOING TO GO ON IN THE
ECONOMY AND THUS THE STOCK
MARKET, THAT MONEY IS GOING TO
COME OUT OF FIXED INCOME AND IN
THE STOCKS ALONG WITH MONEY ON
THE SIDELINES OR SITTING IN CASH
AND THAT'S GOING TO CAUSE A
MARKET MELTDOWN.
RIGHT?
WE DON'T HAVE TO HAVE A DEBATE
WHY MONEY WAS GOING INTO FIXED
INCOME
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS --
>> THE REASON WHY IT MATTERS IS
BECAUSE THE QUESTION IS WHEN
DOES THE MONEY COME BACK, AND
WHERE DOES IT COME FROM AND
WHERE DOES IT GO TO?
IF YOU HAVE SOME SENSE OF WHY
THE FLOWS ARE MOVING
SO IF YOU SAY TO THE AVERAGE
PERSON ON THE STREET THAT HAS
MONEY INVESTED WITH A MONEY
MANAGER, WHY DID YOUR MONEY
MANAGER TAKE 10% OF YOUR EQUITY
EXPOSURE AND PUT IT INTO TLT OR
IEI LAST MONTH, THEY HAVE NO
CLUE
IT'S NOT A DECISION BEING MADE
BY THE END INVESTOR.
THESE ARE DISCRETIONARY
ACCOUNTS, CALL AMERITRADE
INSTITUTIONAL, SCHAUB, PERSONAL
FIDELITY
ASK THEM ABOUT FLOWS AND THEY
WILL TELL YOU THIS HAPPENS ALL
THE TIME AND IT'S NOT ABOUT AN
ECONOMIC REDICTION.
>> GOOD, GREAT
DO YOU AGREE OR DISAGREE WITH
LARRY FINK
>> TOTALLY AGREE WITH HIM.
>> AS THE RIGHT CALL.
>> WHY DO WE NEED TO SPEND ALL
OF THIS TIME DEBATING WHY THE
MONEY MOVED THERE IF YOU AGREE
IT'S GOING TO COME OUT OF WHERE
IT WENT AND CAUSE A FURTHER
MARKET MELTUP?
THAT'S THE BOTTOM LINE
WE CAN DEBATE IT FOR FIVE HOURS.
>> I DON'T KNOW IT HAS TO.
I'M MAKING THE POINT PEOPLE ARE
NOT EXPRESSING ECONOMIC POINTS
OF VIEW.
WHAT'S ACTUALLY HAPPENING IS
POSITIONS BEING MOVED IN ETFs
AND PEOPLE ARE THEN LOOKING AT
THE BOND MARKET FOR A SIGNAL
THAT WILL NEVER ARRIVE.
>> WE CAN DO THIS, WE WILL
CONTINUE THE MARKET CONVERSATION
IN A SECOND.
THERE'S OTHER BIG NEWS
HAPPENING.
AS ALL OF YOU KNOW TODAY THE
BIGGEST OF WHICH IS THE RELEASE
OF THE MUELLER REPORT.
REPORTERS STILL PORING THROUGH
IT AS WE SPEAK
AND WE'RE LIVE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE NOW.
>> WE'RE GETTING OUR FIRST LOOK
INSIDE THE MUELLER REPORT AND SO
ARE MANY OFFICIALS HERE AT THE
WHITE HOUSE WHO HAVE NOT SEEN IT
BEFORE
WHAT WE'RE TOLD IS THE REACTION
INSIDE THE WHITE HOUSE IS
UPBEAT
STAFFERS I HAVE SPOKEN TO SEEM
TO BE IN A GOOD MOOD TODAY
THE PRESIDENT OFFERED HIS FIRST
REACTION IN AN UNRELATED EVENT
EARLIER THIS MORNING HERE AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
HERE'S WHAT HE HAD TO SAY.
>> I'M HAVING A GOOD DAY TOO
IT'S CALLED NO COLLUSION, NO
OBSTRUCTION.
THIS SHOULD NEVER HAPPEN TO
ANOTHER PRESIDENT AGAIN, THIS
HOAX.
>> THE PRESIDENT EXPRESSING SOME
FRUSTRATION THAT THE
INVESTIGATION HAPPENED IN THE
FIRST PLACE, BUT HAPPY WITH THE
RESULTS HERE TODAY, AS OUTLINED
BY THE ATTORNEY GENERAL AND NOW
IN THE MUELLER REPORT, WHICH WAS
AVAILABLE ONLINE
A COUPLE OF HIGHLIGHTS TO BRING
TO YOU, SCOTT, AS WE GO THROUGH,
ONE IS THIS DRAMATIC MOMENT IN
THE OVAL OFFICE RELATED HERE IN
THE MUELLER REPORT THE MOMENT OF
PRESIDENT LEARNED THAT A SPECIAL
COUNSEL HAD BEEN APPOINTED
ACCORDING TO THE CONTEMPORANEOUS
NOTES BEING TAKEN, ATTORNEY
GENERAL SESSIONS STEPPED OUT OF
THE OVAL OFFICE TO GET THE
OFFICE FROM ROD ROSENSTEIN
TELLING HIM THAT HAD HAPPENED,
CAME BACK IN THE ROOM AND
INFORMED THE PRESIDENT
ACCORDING TO THE NOTES, THE
PRESIDENT SLUMPED DOWN IN HIS
CHAIR AND SAID OH, MY GOD, THIS
IS TERRIBLE.
THIS IS THE END OF MY
PRESIDENCY
I'M F'd, HE SAID, USING THE
EXPLETIVE THERE.
SO THE PRESIDENT EXPRESSING A
LITTLE DISMAY AND THEN
IMMEDIATELY DEMANDING THE
RESIGNATION OF ATTORNEY GENERAL
SESSIONS, BLAMING HIM FOR THE
APPOINTMENT OF THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL IN THE WAKE OF THE
PRESIDENT'S FIRING OF THE FBI
DIRECTOR
THAT'S ONE OF THE SORTS OF V
VIGNETTES YOU START TO SEE
COMING OUT OF THE MUELLER
REPORT
A COUPLE HIGHLIGHTS TO BRING
YOU, AS WE KNOW, MUELLER DID NOT
MAKE A PROSECUTORIAL JUDGMENT IN
TERMS OF OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE,
ONE OF THE KEY ELEMENTS PEOPLE
ARE FOCUSED ON HERE.
ALSO THE PRESIDENT ASKED WHITE
HOUSE COUNSEL DONE McGHAN AT THE
TIME TO INTERVENE WITH THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
THE PRESIDENT ALSO ASKED THE
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL TO INTERVENE
WITH THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT.
ULTIMATELY THIS INVESTIGATION
DID NOT ESTABLISH THE PRESIDENT
ASKED INTELLIGENCE LEADERS TO
INTERFERE WITH THE FBI PROBE
THE INVESTIGATORS ALSO CONCLUDE
THE PRESIDENT'S WRITTEN ANSWERS
INADEQUATE AND ULTIMATELY
SUGGESTED THEY DIDN'T GO FORWARD
WITH A SUBPOENA TO THE PRESIDENT
IN TERMS OF HIS TESTIMONY IN
PERSON BECAUSE THEY WERE RUNNING
OUT OF TIME.
IT WAS A LATE STAGE IN THE
INVESTIGATION AND NEGOTIATIONS
HAD GONE ON FOR JUST ABOUT A
YEAR OR MORE AT THAT POINT
SO ULTIMATELY THE PRESIDENT
NEVER DID SIT DOWN WITH ROBERT
MUELLER'S TEAM HERE, SCOTT.
>> YOU KNOW, THERE'S SO MUCH
INTERESTING IN THIS REPORT,
INCLUDING THINGS THAT WE'RE
LEARNING FOR THE FIRST TIME AS
YOU REFERENCED
THE PRESIDENT'S REACTION ON THE
APPOINTMENT OF THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL.
MOST INTERESTING WHAT YOU
PLAYED, THE PRESIDENT'S REACTION
NOT EXACTLY MATCHING UP IN WHAT
WAS DELIVERED IN THE MUELLER
REPORT
I READ ANOTHER SECTION, AND I'M
QUOTING HERE, THIS IS FROM MR.
MUELLER.
IF WE HAD CONFIDENCE AFTER A
THOROUGH INVESTIGATION OF THE
FACTS THAT THE PRESIDENT CLEARLY
DID NOT COMMIT OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE, WE WOULD SO STATE
BASED UPON THE FACTS IN THE
APPLICABLE LEGAL STANDARDS,
HOWEVER, WE'RE UNABLE TO REACH
THAT JUDGMENT.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET DOWN TO WHAT
BECOMES BEHAVIOR THAT MAYBE
DIDN'T REACH THE LEVEL OF
CRIMINALITY BUT WAS NONETHELESS
IMPROPER ON MANY LEVELS.
>> AND WHAT THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
DOES HERE IS SORT OF STRADDLE
THE QUESTION ON WHETHER LEAVING
TO DECIDE IF IT'S IMPROPER,
WHICH IS NOT BUT ILLEGAL FOR HIM
TO DECIDE.
AND THERE'S EVIDENCE ON BOTH
SIDES OF THAT QUESTION AS BILL
BARR PUT IT.
THE QUESTION THEN BECOMES WHAT
DO YOU DO WITH THAT?
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL MENTIONS
CONGRESS A NUMBER OF TIMES
OF COURSE, CONGRESS COULD LOOK
AT THIS AND DETERMINE, YOU KNOW
WHAT, THIS MAY NOT BE ILLEGAL
BUT IT SURE IS TERRIBLE AND
POLITICALLY WE THINK IT SHOULD
NEVER HAPPEN SO WE'RE GOING TO
MOVE FORWARD WITH IMPEACHMENT.
THAT'S NOT WHAT WE ARE HEARING
UP ON CAPITOL HILL TODAY FROM
DEMOCRATS WHO ARE IN CONTROL OF
THE HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES AND
CERTAINLY FROM REPUBLICANS WHO
ARE IN CONTROL OF THE SENATE
SO THE EXPECTATION HERE IS THIS
REPORT IS OUT THERE NOW FOR THE
WORLD TO SEE AND THE PRESIDENT'S
CONDUCT IS OUT THERE FOR PEOPLE
TO EXAMINE
AND VOTERS WILL MAKE A
DETERMINATION IN 2020 BECAUSE IT
DOES NOT SEEM AT THIS MOMENT, AS
I STAND HERE NOW, THAT
IMPEACHMENT IS IN THE OFFING
FROM THIS PRESIDENT.
>> SOME OF THE ACTIONS LAID OUT
BY THE SPECIAL COUNSEL OF THE
PRESIDENT'S SON DON JR. WILL BE
PARSED MANY WAYS AS WELL
AYMAN, WE WILL GET BACK TO YOU
AS NECESSARY
THANK YOU FOR COMING ON.
AYMAN JABBERS, STILL GOING
THROUGH WHAT IS A MORE THAN
400-PAGE MUELLER REPORT.
LET'S GET BACK TO THE MARKET
CONVERSATION
I DIDN'T HEAR FROM YOU YET
WHERE DO YOU WEIGH IN RELATIVE
TO WHAT YOU HEARD HERE
>> I THINK YOU HAVE TO LOOK AT
THIS RATHER SIMPLISTICALLY
IF YOU MADE A LIST OF ALL OF THE
CONDITIONS EVERYONE ON THE SHOW
WAS TALKING ABOUT INCLUDING
MYSELF IN JANUARY, ALL OF THAT
LIST HAS BEEN ERADICATED BY THE
MARKETPLACE ITSELF
BACK IN DECEMBER THERE WAS NO
ONE HIGH YIELD OFFERING, NOT
ONE, ZERO.
OKAY
YOU BASICALLY THE FIRST QUARTER
OF 2019 HAD MONEY FLOW INTO
EVERY PLACE.
TAKE A LOOK AT THE MSCI, THE
PERFORMANCE THERE, ALL ASSET
CLASSES ARE RISING
WE ARE NOW PRESENTED WITH A
SITUATION, WHERE DO WE GO FROM
HERE
AND YOU ARE AT THE MOST CRITICAL
COMPONENT OF THE EARNINGS
SEASON, THE NEXT TWO WEEKS,
WE'RE GOING TO GET FACEBOOK.
WE'RE GOING TO GET AMAZON.
WE'RE GOING TO GET TECHNOLOGY
STORY.
>> NEXT WEEK, BY THE WAY, SINCE
YOU BRING IT UP, 142 S&P
COMPANIES, VIRTUALLY EVERY
MARQUEE NAME THAT WE TALK ABOUT,
IS GOING TO GIVE THEIR EARNINGS
REPORTS NEXT WEEK.
>> A REFERENDUM ON EARNINGS.
>> LET ME FINISH MY THOUGHT.
I DON'T THINK IT'S A MATTER OF
WHERE WE ARE NOW, DO WE GO TO
THE HIGHS.
THE NASDAQ HIGH IS 8109.
WE'RE AT 8000.
WE'RE GETTING THERE.
IF IT WASN'T FOR HEALTH CARE,
WE'D BE ABOVE THE S&P HIGH RIGHT
NOW.
IT'S A MATTER OF HOW MUCH DO YOU
ACCELERATE THROUGH IT ONCE YOU
HEAR THE TECHNOLOGY REPORTS.
I AGREE WITH WHAT I'M SAYING
ABOUT JOSH'S COMMENTS ABOUT
FOCUS OF GROWTH.
GROWTH IS BACK ONCE AGAIN.
LET'S NOT FORGET WE HAVE A
20-POINT BASIS HIGH MOVE IN TEN
YEARS IN BASICALLY THE COURSE OF
THREE WEEKS.
THAT'S SIGNALING SOMETHING TO
THE MARKETPLACE.
>> LET ME DO THIS, WE CAN
ACTUALLY BRING YOU THESE RAPID
UPDATES STEVE LIESMAN GETS ON
THE ECONOMY.
HE HAS ANOTHER ONE
THERE'S GOOD ECONOMIC DATA YET
AGAIN TODAY, STEVE
WE MENTIONED RETAIL SALES
EARLIER.
GDP TRACKING HIGHER YESTERDAY.
HOW ABOUT NOW?
>> NOW WILL OCCASIONALLY TWO
DAYS IN A ROW GOING UP BY .4%
YESTERDAY AND .3% TODAY.
WE'RE UP 3.4% ON THE TRACKING
FORECAST FOR THE FIRST QUARTER
THAT IS UP .3% ON THE BACK OF
THAT BETTER-THAN-EXPECTED RETAIL
REPORT THIS MORNING.
THE CONSUMER GIVEN UP FOR DEAD A
LITTLE TOO QUICKLY HERE.
CONSUMPTION IN THE FIRST QUARTER
RUNNING GOOD
LET'S LOOK AT THE OUTLOOK FROM
THE SECOND QUARTER, 2 1/2%
IF YOU'RE HOLDING YOUR BREATH
FOR A CUT, THE FED AIN'T CUTTING
IT, 2.45%.
THAT'S HALF POINT OR BERT OF
WHAT THEIR VIEW OF POTENTIAL
GROWTH IS.
HERE'S SOME OF THE FORECAST,
ATLANTA FED AND MOODIES AT 2.8
ON THE HIGH SIDE ACTION 2.6.
ACTION, GOLDMAN, OXFORD RIGHT
THERE.
AND WE HAVE GONE FROM A 1% PRINT
ON THIS WRAP IT UP DATE IN EARLY
MARCH ALL THE WAY UP BY 1.4
PERCENTAGE POINTS UP TO 2.4,
SCOTT, ON THE BACK OF THE BETTER
TRADE DATA YESTERDAY AND BETTER
RETAIL SALES DATA TODAY.
>> GOOD STUFF.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> LET'S BRING IN TOM LIENIO,
HEAD OF RESEARCH AT FUN SCRATCH.
WE HAVE BETTER ECONOMIC DATA
BETTER EARNINGS, WE CAN SAY
CLEARLY.
YET YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A SWIFT
AND COULD BE QUICK PULLBACK IN
THE MARKET BECAUSE OF WHAT WE
DISCUSSED SPECIFICALLY AT THIS
DESK
>> YES
HEALTH CARE IS A HUGE SECTOR FOR
INSTITUTIONAL MANAGER.
IT'S SAYING THEIR BACON LAST
YEAR, HEALTH CARE IS 65% OF THE
PROSPECTUS, 60% GROWTH AND
THAT'S HEDGE FUND'S TRAFFIC.
THERE'S REAL POLITICAL RISK
EMERGING FOR THE GROUP FOR THE
FIRST TIME
I THINK YOU GUYS MENTIONED IT.
IT LOOKS LIKE EARLY '93.
IF IT'S 60% OF WHAT YOU TRAFFIC
IN, THEY'RE GOING TO START TO
ROTATE INTO GROWTH CYCLICALS,
WHICH IS NOT HEALTH CARE
I THINK BECAUSE SOMEONE SAID YOU
HAVE TO TAKE A HUGE ALLOCATION
NOT OF ONE GROUP ON A LIGHT
VOLUME MARKET, I THINK IT
CREATES A LOT OF TURBULENCE.
>> SO MANY OTHER SECTORS ARE
WORKING.
YESTERDAY I THINK I STARTED THE
PROGRAM BY NOTING X SECTOR
ALL-TIME HIGH, Y SECTOR ALL-TIME
HIGH AND ON AND ON AND ON.
AND WHO CARES?
>> ANYONE WHO HAS HEALTH CARE
EXPOSURE, 14% BURT FOR HEDGE
FUNDS AND GROWTH MANAGERS, IT'S
50% TO 60% OF WHAT THEY OWN.
IT'S A BIG DEAL EVERYTHING ELSE
IS WORKING AND HEALTH CARE IS
NOT.
BUT THAT ROTATION WILL BE TOUGH.
WHO'S THE NATURAL BUYER TO COME
IN AND BUY THESE
>> I WILL DISAGREE ON A COUPLE
OF THINGS.
NUMBER ONE, HEDGE FUNDS ARE A
RELATIVELY SMALL PART OF THE
EQUITY MARKET.
NUMBER TWO THEY'RE
UNDERINVESTORS AS EVERYONE IS
SAYING
I DON'T THINK IT'S A BIG DEAL
FOR THEM
ANY BIGGER DEAL THAN IT IS THE
BIG INSTITUTIONS, WHO ARE THE
MAJOR HEALTH CARE HOLDERS.
GROWTH, YES.
GROWTH IS THERE BY HEALTH CARE
IT'S NOT ACCIDENTAL TECHS START
TO PERFORM THE LAST FEW WEEKS AS
HEALTH CARE UNDERPERFORMS.
SO THERE'S A ROTATION I HAVE TO
FIND GROWTH.
I'M UNCOMFORTABLE WITH HEALTH
CARE GIVEN THE POLITICAL
CLIMATE.
GUESS WHAT, WE SAW THIS EXACT
THING FROM HILLARY CLINTON
WE SAW THE EXACT THING FROM
BERNIE SANDERS AD NAUSEAM SINCE
HE WAS IN VERMONT AND IT'S NOT
GOING TO WORK.
SO THAT'S WHY IT'S AN
OPPORTUNITY.
EVERY TIME WE TALK ABOUT THE
MARKET, WE'LL TALK ABOUT CAN THE
MARKET MOVE WITHOUT FANG
CAN THE MARKET MOVE WITHOUT
FINANCIALS
YES, THE MARKET MOVED.
CAN THE MARKET MOVE WITHOUT
HEALTH CARE?
13%, OF COURSE IT CAN.
YOU WILL SEE MONEY GO BACK.
>> OBVIOUSLY, IT HAS.
>> IN THE BIGGER CONTEXT I'M
BULLISH FOR THE YEAR
BUT DO I THINK THAT -- CAN THE
S&P ADVANCE 100 POINTS WITH
HEALTH CARE UNDERPERFORMING,
IT'S POSSIBLE.
>> WHY SHOULD I CARE, TOM?
HOW CAN I PINPOINT THE EXACT
POINT IN TIME WE GET A
CORRECTION IF IT'S ONLY GOING TO
BOUNCE BACK?
>> ACTUALLY I THIS IT'S
IMPORTANT FROM A STOCK
PERSPECTIVE.
FOR US WE THINK THIS IS AN
OPPORTUNITY TO ADD TO GROWTH
CYCLICALS WHETHER IT'S DISNEY,
GOOGLE, BLACKROCK
>> PRETTY STELLAR LIST
THESE ARE THE STOCKS, BY THE
WAY, THIS IS PART OF THE THESIS.
WE WANT TO LET PEOPLE KNOW THAT.
THIS IS NOT SORT OF RUN FOR THE
HILLS.
THIS ROTATION OUT OF AN
UNDERPERFORMING SECTOR LIKE
HEALTH CARE WILL PRESENT BROAD
OPPORTUNITY IN THE BLUE CHIP
NAMES THAT MANY FOLLOW, DISNEY,
APPLE.
YOU LOOK DOWN THE LIST HERE,
FACEBOOK
I WILL NOT SAY IBM
>> THERE'S A MISTAKE THAT IBM'S
ON THAT LIST
I DON'T THINK GROWTH OR QUALITY.
>> GROWTH AND QUALITY CYCLICALS
SO IT'S A HODGEPODGE OF BOTH
BUT THOSE HAVE ZERO PERCENT
WEIGHT IN HEALTH CARE.
>> AND I THINK STEVE MAKES A
POINT ABOUT POLITICAL STUFF.
I DON'T KNOW IF I 100% AGREE
THOUGH THAT THE MARKET WILL
SHAKE IT OFF THAT QUICKLY THIS
TIME.
>> IT'S NOT.
>> SO TWO NIGHTS AGO SOMETHING
EXTRAORDINARY HAPPENED THAT I
DON'T THINK IS A STOCK MARKET
STORY BUT IT COULD BECOME.
BERNIE SANDERS DID A TOWN HALL
ON FOX NEWS.
2.8 MILLION VIEWERS TUNED IN
THESE ARE FOX VIEWERS.
THIS IS NOT FIDEL CASTRO AND
FRIENDS.
AND THE PORTION OF WHAT HE HAD
TO SAY THAT WAS MOST ECHOED
THROUGHOUT CONSERVATIVE MEDIA
AND SOCIAL MEDIA, THE PORTION
THAT PEOPLE SEEMED TO HAVE FOUND
THE MOST COMMON CAUSE WITH OUT
OF EVERYTHING HE SAID WAS ABOUT
HEALTH CARE, PRIVATE VERSUS
GOVERNMENT, AND BENEFITS
AND NO ONE IN THAT AUDIENCE
WOULD SAY WE LIKE SOCIALISM BUT
MOST OF THEM ARE LIVING ON SOME
FORM OF SOCIALISM IN SOME
PORTION OF THEIR LIFE.
AND IT'S THE GOOD KIND OF
SOCIALISM, THE KIND THAT WE
DON'T LIKE TO TALK ABOUT AND SAY
IT'S THAT.
BUT I THINK THAT IF YOU SEE THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY GET SUBSUMED BY
ITS FURTHEST LEFT WING AND YOU
CONTINUE TO SEE ALL OF THE
OXYGEN SUCKED OUT OF THE AIR BY
PEOPLE LIKE AOC AND BERNIE
SANDERS, AND THAT IS WHAT'S
HAPPENING SO FAR IN THE
PRIMARIES, THAT WILL WEIGH ON
THIS SEGMENT OF THE MARKET
THAT WILL CONTINUE TO BE A
SOURCE OF CONSTERNATION FOR
INVESTORS.
I THINK THERE WILL BE MULTIPLES
OF PEOPLE THROG PAY AND LOOK AT
THE STOCK OF INSURANCE
PROVIDERS, THEY'VE BEEN
ABSOLUTELY HAMMERED.
SO IT'S A BROAD DISPARITY IN
PERFORMANCE FOR THE WHOLE SECTOR
BUT WHEN YOU GO INDUSTRY GROUP,
THERE'S REAL PAIN THERE IN
COMPANIES IN WHAT PEOPLE WERE
CALLING BLUE CHIPS NOT VERY LONG
AGO.
>> HOW DO WE THINK ABOUT THIS IN
THE OVERALL FUNDAMENTAL
OPPORTUNITY?
I HEAR WHAT YOU'RE SAYING, M
MULTIPLES CAN BE CONSTRAINED BY
ALL OF THE POLITICAL NOISE AND
THAT'S NOT GOING AWAY IN THE
NEAR TERM.
THAT SAID THE FUNDAMENTALS OF
THE SECTOR LOOKS REALLY SOLID.
THE EARNINGS ACROSS DIFFERENT
INDUSTRY GROUPS, NOT JUST 2019
BUT 2020
WE ALSO KNOW THERE'S A SECULAR
TAIL WIND BEHIND A LOT OF DEMAND
FOR PRODUCT SERVICES IN SOFTWARE
IN THAT SPACE.
HEALTH CARE SOFTWARE AND
TECHNOLOGY IS SOMETHING PEOPLE
UNDERRECOGNIZE AS A HUGE GROWTH
OPPORTUNITY, I THINK.
>> SO YOU'RE LOOKING AT THE
OTHER SIDE OF HEALTH CARE?
YOU'RE TAKING MORE POSITIVE
VIEW, IT SOUNDS TO ME.
>> SHE'S SAYING OPPORTUNITY.
>> OPPORTUNITY
THERE'S ANOTHER ELEMENT TO THOSE
IT TOO.
>> AND OTHERS ARE SUGGESTING --
SORRY TO INTERRUPT YOU, VALUE
AND DON'T GO THERE
WHY BOTHER
>> I DON'T THINK IT CAN BE A
VALUE TRAP
I 100% AGREE WITH YOU, ARE YOU
GOING TO CONTINUE TO THROW YOUR
MONEY AT NAMES HITTING 52-WEEK
HIGHS UNLESS YOU THINK THEY'RE
GOING TO CLIMB THROUGH THEM?
OR ARE YOU LOOKING FOR
OPPORTUNITIES?
I DON'T THINK IT'S A TRAP
NECESSARILY.
HEALT
HEALTH CARE WILL BE THERE.
WE HAVE AN AGING SOCIETY
HEALTH CARE, WE NEED IT.
>> 174 MILLION PEOPLE INSURED
WITH PRIVATE HEALTH CARE
WILL THAT BE THE CASE FOUR YEARS
FROM NOW
OR WILL A SIGNIFICANT PORTION OF
THAT IF THE DEMOCRATS KEEP
CONTROL OF THE HOUSE AND SOMEHOW
GAIN EITHER THE WHITE HOUSE OR
THE SENATE, THAT IS WHAT
PEOPLE -- PEOPLE ARE LOOKING AT
2020 AND BEYOND NOW.
THE QUESTION IS, HOW MUCH
FURTHER AWAY DO WE GET FROM
PRIVATE HEALTH CARE FOR HOW MANY
HOUSEHOLDS AND WHAT DOES THAT DO
FOR THE ECONOMICS OF THE SECTOR?
HOW MANY MARKETS MIGHT HAVE
SINGLE PAIR?
>> BUT THERE'S A WHOLE REST OF
THE SECTOR THAT LOOKS REALLY
ATTRACTIVE BOTH IN THE NEAR
TERM --
>> BUT THAT'S WHERE THE
OPPORTUNITY IS CREATED
PEOPLE CAN SAY THE SECTOR IS BAD
BUT WHERE IN THE SECTOR?
>> THE SUB SECTORS.
>> IF YOU TAKE A STEP BACK AND
LOOK AT THE INSTITUTIONAL WORLD
WHO MASSIVELY YOET WEIGHTED
HEALTH CARE AND IT'S 60%, 70% OF
WHAT THEY TRAFFIC IN, IT'S STUFF
TO STAY I WILL STICK WITH THAT
60% WITH 12 MONTHS OF
UNCERTAINTY.
IF IT SHRINKS, IT'S A HUGE WIN
FOR CYCLICAL TRADE BUT IT'S
SLOPPY.
>> IT'S SLOPPY, AND I CAN TELL
YOU TALKING TO A HEDGE FUND IN
HEALTH CARE.
THEY'RE NOT REACTING TO THE FOX
BERNIE SANDERS APPEARANCE.
THEY'RE NOT REACTING TO THE
NARRATIVE AROUND WHAT COULD
HAPPEN IN 2020
THEY'RE REACTING TO THE FACT
HEALTH CARE IS DOWN 7% THE LAST
14 DAYS.
>> OR MORE
>> THEY'RE REACTING SPECIFICALLY
TO THE PRICE
THE MODELS, THE AIL GA RHYTHMIC
MODELS, NOT THE OTHER NONSENSE,
THE ACTUAL MODELS DRIVE THEIR
DECISIONS AND THOSE DECISIONS
ARE BEING MADE WHEN YOU SEE AN
OUTSIDE 7% MOVE TO GET OUT OF
IT
ARE THERE OPPORTUNITIES IN THAT?
100%
I SAID IT YESTERDAY.
McKESSON, NOTHING DO WITH THE
MEDICAL DEVICES, THAT'S WHERE
THE OPPORTUNITY IS UNLESS YOU
BELIEVE IT'S GOING DOWN ANOTHER
7%.
>> LET ME ASK YOU THIS, YOU SAY
MORE BROADLY YOU'RE POSITIVE ON
STOCKS, RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> FOR THE DISTANCE OF THE YEAR.
DO YOU AGREE WITH LARRY FINK
ARE YOU GOING TO GET THIS
MELT-UP?
A LOT OF NONBELIEVERS WHO WILL
BECOME BELIEVERS IN THE MARKET,
THE RALLY?
>> YEAH, YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE
THERE'S A LOT OF DRY POWDER.
THERE'S TON IT SOUNDS LIKE EVEN
JOSH WITH MONEY PARKED IN FIXED
INCOME, PEOPLE SAVE ALMOST A
TRILLION A YEAR.
NONE HAD GONE INTO EQUITIES.
CREDIT HAD THE FOURTH BEST YEAR
IN 30 YEARS.
INCREDIBLE YEAR IN HIGH YIELD.
CATCH-UP TRADE THERE
AND I THINK ECONOMIC MOMENTUM IS
IMPROVING IN THE SECOND HALF.
>> DOESN'T ALL OF THE POWDER YOU
JUST REFERENCED OFFSET WHATEVER
NEGATIVES COME FROM A PULL FROM
HEALTH CARE IN A ROTATION INTO
THESE OTHER MORE ADVANTAGEOUS
AREAS?
>> I THINK BY 2019 IT'S AN UP
25% YEAR
I THINK S&P 3100 IS WHAT THE
BASE CASE FOR PEOPLE SHOULD BE.
>> BASE CASE
OKAY.
>> BUT CAN WE REVISIT 2700 OR
I THINK IT'S POSSIBLE.
>> WHAT'S BEST CASE?
>> I THINK BEST CASE WOULD BE WE
GET TOWARDS AN 18 MULTIPLE
BECAUSE PEOPLE REALIZE WE ARE
LATE CYCLE
SO YOU COULD BE 33, 34
BUT WE THINK THIS LOOKS LIKE '09
AND TRACKING LIKE '09.
>> I NOTICE HE HAD SURGERY ON
HIS KNEE, I'M WONDERING IF HE'S
STILL ON PAINKILLERS
>> STEVE
>> LOOK, I --
>> WHY NOT
TELL ME WHY NOT.
>> I THINK 18 MULTIPLE IS KIND
OF HIGH AND I THINK WE ARE LATE
CYCLE.
WHEN YOU STILL HAVE THE ISSUE OF
GERMAN NUMBERS AGAIN TODAY, DOWN
AGAIN.
SO YOU HAVE MANUFACTURING
NUMBERS DOWN AGAIN
>> YOU SAID THIS EARLIER, WHO
CARES?
WHY SHOULD I CARE?
>> I DO LOOK AT THE LOCATION
WITH HEALTH CARE AS AN
OPPORTUNITY, MY NOTE THIS
MORNING, PLACES TO GO.
THIS WILL NOT GO ANYWHERE.
BERNIE SANDERS DID THIS STUDY
WHEN HE WAS IN VERMONT IN 2011
AND WHAT HE NEEDS TO GET THIS
DONE IS RAISE TAXES, DOUBLING
TAX RATES ON PEOPLE MAKING
$250,000 OR OVER
YOU THINK DEMOCRATS WILL DO
THAT
>> HOW ABOUT THE FIRST QUARTER
IS GENERALLY WEAK, WEAKER THAN
THE REMAINDER OF THE YEAR.
>> OBVIOUSLY, IT LOOKS TO BE
COMING IN BETTER-THAN-EXPECTED
LIESMAN'S WRAPPED IT UP THE LAST
TWO DAYS AND GDP BUMPS BY THE
BIG HOUSES OVER THE LAST COUPLE
OF DAYS THAT SUGGESTS THE
ECONOMY IS BETTER THAN MAYBE
PEOPLE THOUGHT
WHAT IF EARNINGS FOLLOWED SUIT
WHAT IF WE'RE NOT GOING THROUGH
THE CYCLE AS YOU THINK
>> LOOK, WE'VE VET EARNINGS
EXPECTATIONS WITHOUT VETTING THE
MARKET -- RESETTING THE MARKETS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU CANNOT SAY THINGS ARE
MOVING ALONG LIKE THEY WERE AND
ALL OF THE FEARS IN DECEMBER
WERE MISS PLACED
THEY WEREN'T MISPLACED
GROWTH HAS SLOWED DOWN
WE WILL SEE GUIDANCE GOING
FORWARD.
TO ME WATER FINDS ITS OWN LEVEL.
>> I GOT YOU
BUT HONEYWELL SAYS, OKAY, I SEE
YOU.
I GET YOU BUT I'M RAISING MY
GUIDANCE AND UNITED UNION
PACIFIC SAYS I'M RAISING MY
GUIDANCE
CEO WAS ON THE NETWORK EARLIER
THINGS ARE GOOD.
>> I THINK IN THE RAILS HE SAID
THINGS WERE A LITTLE SLOW.
>> HE WAS --
>> YOU JUST SAID THERE WAS A
SLOWDOWN
I WAS LISTENING TO THE
INTERVIEW.
>> I WAS TOO.
>> BUT THINGS ARE BETTER
THEY ARE RUNNING IT BETTER
BUT THERE'S STRENGTH IN THE
ECONOMY.
NOBODY'S COMING OUT SAYING THE
ECONOMY IS REALLY WEAK
UNITED RENTALS, FWAUK LATER,
GREAT QUARTER.
>> WHAT WAS DOOMSDAY WITH A LOT
OF BLACK CLOUDS ROLLING IN SEEMS
TO BE MORE SUNNY THAN PEOPLE
EXPECTED
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
AND AGAIN, WE LOWERED
EXPECTATIONS SO SUBSTANTIALLY,
RIGHT, SO IT'S LIKE WERE THEY
PLAYING GAMES BECAUSE YOU KNOW
IF YOU MISS, YOU'RE GETTING
PUNISHED IN THIS MARKET RIGHT
NOW.
SO I DO THINK THAT THEY LOWERED
EXPECTATIONS PROBABLY TOO MUCH
AND NOW THEY'RE LIKE OH, WELL
MAYBE WE GOT A LITTLE WIGGLE
ROOM
MAYBE WE WILL LET THEM KNOW
WE'RE DOING BETTER THAN WE
EXPECTED
TRUTH IS THE NUMBERS AND
FUNDAMENTALS ARE THERE FROM THE
ECONOMY.
WE ARE STILL SEEING GROWTH IN
VARIOUS SECTORS OF THE MARKET.
IT IS I DON'T WANT TO SAY THE
COMPANIES ARE DOING WELL ACROSS
ALL SECTORS BUT ULTIMATELY THERE
ARE INDIVIDUAL COMPANIES WITHIN
THOSE THAT YOU CAN FIND
OPPORTUNITIES IN THOSE SUB
SECTORS AND IN THOSE PARTICULAR
NAMES.
>> TOMMY LEE, YOU GET THE LAST
BUT BRIEF WORD
I HAVE TO WRAP IT UP.
>> IF WE'RE LATE CYCLE, THIS IS
A GOOD YEAR AND NEXT YEAR STINKS
BUT MID-CYCLE, IT ENDS ON A GOOD
NOTE AND A POSITIVE.
>> OLD QUESTION WE HAVE TO START
ASKING --
>> WHAT INNING ARE WE IN
>> TOM, THANK YOU.
>>> HERE'S WHAT'S ELSE IS COMING
UP ON "THE HALFTIME REPORT."
>> ONE ANALYST'S CALL ON
MICROSOFT, HE SAID THE STOCK IS
ABOUT TO SURGE MORE THAN 20%
>>> PLUS, WE'LL GET AWE HEAD
INTO NEXT WEEK'S EARNINGS.
ON THE DOCKET, VERIZON, TWITTER,
AT&T, BOEING, CAT, FACEBOOK,
TESLA, AMAZON, FORD, INTEL,
BRISTOL-MYERS, CHEVRON, AND
MORE
>>> BEFORE THE BREAK, WHAT
HAPPENS AFTER THE XLI
INDUSTRIALS INDEX JUMPS 4% OR
MORE IN A MONTH?
WE WILL SHOW UNITED, SOUTHWEST
AND AMERICAN ALL SOAR MORE THAN
3% A WEEK LATER.
FOR MORE GO CNBC.COM
's got that.
Free access to every platform.
Yeah, that too.
I don't want any trade minimums.
Yeah, I totally agree,
they don't have any of those.
I want to know what
I'm paying upfront.
Yes, absolutely.
Do you just say yes
to everything?
Hm. Well I say no to kale.
Mm.
Yeah, they say if you blanch it
it's better,
but that seems like
a lot of work.
No hidden fees.
No platform fees.
No trade minimums.
And yes,
it's all at one low price.
TD Ameritrade.
♪♪
You're turning onto the
street
when you barely
clip a passing car.
Minor accident
—no big deal, right?
Wrong. Your insurance
company is gonna raise
your rate after the other
car got a scratch so small
you coulda fixed
it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that
pen and use it to sign up
with a different
insurance company.
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because of
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>>> I'M CONTESSA BREWER.
HERE'S YOUR CNBC UPDATE.
THE REPORT SAYS PRESIDENT TRUMP
DIRECTED WHITE HOUSE DON McGAHN
TO CALL THE ACTING ATTORNEY
GENERAL AND SAY MUELLER MUST BE
OUSTED BECAUSE HE HAD CONFLICTS
OF INTEREST.
McGHAN REFUSED
THE REPORT DOES NOT CONCLUDE THE
PRESIDENT COMMITTED A CRIME, BUT
DOES NOT EXONERATE HIM
>>> SENATE MAJORITY LEADER MITCH
McCONNELL SAID HE PLANS TO
INCLUDE LEGISLATION TO RAISE THE
MINIMUM WAGE TO BUY TOBACCO
PROJECTS FROM 18 TO 21
NATIONWIDE
I SAID HIS BILL WILL COVER ALL
TOBACCO PRODUCTS, INCLUDING
VAPING DEVICES.
>> IF YOU CAN LEGALLY PURCHASE
AT 21, THERE WOULD BE FEWER
OPPORTUNITIES FOR BABIES TO GET
THEIR HANDS ON THESE DEVICES
>>> INVESTIGATORS ARE
INVESTIGATING A MYSTERIOUS DELI
OUTBREAK OF LIST TIRAS-LIKE
ILLNESSES.
FOUR PEOPLE HAD TO GO TO THE
HOSPITAL ONE PERSON DIED.
>> CONTESSA, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH
>>> MICROSOFT HITTING AN
ALL-TIME HIGH TODAY AND GETTING
A PRICE INCREASE AHEAD OF
EARNINGS OUT NEXT WEEK
WE'VE MADE IT OUR CALL OF THE
DAY.
YOU DON'T NEED TO BE A ROCKET
SCIENTIST TO KNOW IT'S A
FAVORITE STOCK ON THIS DESK BUT
BECAUSE OF THE PRICE TARGET BUMP
AND CONTINUING MOMENTUM BEHIND
IT
YOU OWN IT
>> I DO NOT.
BUT TWO WORDS, I'M SUCH A BIG
F
FAN, SATA.
LEADERSHIP FROM THE CLOUD.
I THINK MY KIDS KNOW THIS, THE
CLOUD IS WHAT WE WILL BE TALKING
ABOUT HERE.
>> I LOVE THE TIGER WOODS
REFERENCES KEEP COMING IN AS
PEOPLE PUT UPGRADES ON SINCE
TIGER WOODS WON THE MASTERS.
>> THEY SAY IT'S ROARING THROUGH
2019 LIKE TIGER ON THE 16th.
REMEMBER, THE PAR 3, ROLLS DOWN
THE LITTLE SLOPE, WITHIN A
COUPLE OF FEET
MAKES THE BIRDIE
GOES UP BY TWO SHOTS
>> I LOVE THE STOCK, AS I
MENTIONED EARLIER, I BOUGHT
OPTIONS LAST WEEK, CAUSE ON IT
AND SOLD SOME BECAUSE THEY DID
WELL IN THE SHORT PERIOD OF
TIME
HE'S DOING GREAT
HE'S TURNED INTO A COMPLETE
SUBSCRIPTION MODEL, FASCINATING,
ATTACKING ALL OTHER PRODUCTS
THEY DIDN'T HAVE IN THEIR
QUIVER
I THINK THERE'S MORE GROIJWTH TO
COME.
>> THE BEST STRATEGY AND STYLE
OF MICROSOFT IS HIGH GROWTH
STRATEGY WITHOUT THE HYPER
VOLATILITY
IF YOU OWN IT, WHICH I DO, IT'S
BEEN VERY EASY TO OWN THIS STOCK
FROM THE MID-'60s, WHICH IS
WHERE I OWN IT FROM, AND OTHER
PORTFOLIO MANAGERS
YOU DO NOT HAVE THE HYPER
VOLATILITY
YOU HAVE A PHENOMENAL MANAGEMENT
TEAM
YOU HAVE A DIVERSIFIED BUSINESS
THAT SHOWS ORGANIC GROWTH.
YES, I CAN SEE IT AT 150
AND WE'RE OFF TO THE RACES
TALKING ABOUT THE TRILLION
DOLLAR MARKET CAP.
APPLE 960, MICROSOFT AROUND 940.
THEY'RE BOTH HEADED THERE.
>> YOU LOOK AT THIS AS A GREAT
TURNAROUND STORY
IS TURNAROUND THE RIGHT WORD
I MEAN FROM -- I'M CURIOUS HOW
THE DESK VIEWS THIS.
IT'S NOT LIKE THE COMPANY WAS
DOING BAD.
THE STOCK WAS SO STUCK IN THE
MUD FOR SO LONG, THEY WERE SO
TIED TO ONE PARTICULAR PART OF
THE BUSINESS
AND THROUGH NADELLA AND THE
LEADERSHIP OF HIM AND HIS
EXECUTIVE TEAM AND BEING NOW IN
THE RIGHT PLACE, IS THAT A
TURNAROUND
>> I THINK IT'S A TYPICAL FACE
OF FRESH EYES.
NEW FOUNDER, FRESH EYES SAYING
WHAT CAN WE DO HERE?
WE WILL TAKE MICROSOFT, THEIR
PRODUCTS, AND CONTINUE TO
UPGRADE THE PRODUCT OUTLOOK AND
WE CAN PUT IT ON A SUBSCRIPTION
BASE RATHER THAN JUST SELLING A
LICENSE FOR IT
SO YOU'VE GOT TO KEEP GOING.
WE CAN TAKE OTHER THINGS THAT
THEY DO LIKE THE CLOUD WAS SEEN
TO BE AN EASY ONE AND EXPAND
THERE.
THE CLOUD I MORE WORRY ABOUT
BECAUSE IT'S A COMMODITY OF
BUSINESS AND YOU SEE REAL
PRICING.
BUT THEY KEEP ADDING PRODUCTS,
THEY KEEP ADDING FUNCTIONALITY,
SO YOU HAVE TO GO AFTER IT TO
MATCH THE TECHNOLOGICAL ADVANCES
AROUND YOU
AND THAT'S KEY
THAT'S THE FRESH EYES.
>> JOSH?
>> YEAH, I THINK --
>> I CAN'T EVEN REMEMBER.
>> THE WHOLE COUNTRY OWNS IT
IT'S LIKE THE SECOND BIGGEST
STOCK IN THE WORLD
IT'S IN EVERY INDEX.
I DON'T HAVE AN INDIVIDUAL
OVERWEIGHT TO IT, I WISH I DID
BUT YOU CAN'T ON EVERYTHING.
THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT, I THINK
FRESH EYES
THE WEE TURNAROUND WHEN OBAMA
WAS RUNNING IT FROM WHEN HE TOOK
OVER IN 2000 TO WHEN HE LEFT
THAT'S NOT REALLY A TURNAROUND
THE TAKEAWAY IS WHAT PRICE YOU
PAID
IF YOU BOUGHT IT IN 1999, 2000
YOU PAID SEVEN TIMES EARNINGS
FOR MICROSOFT HN TO GET DOWN TO
12 TIMES EARNINGS.
SO IT TRIPLED EARNINGS BUT THE
MULTIPLE WAS SO HIGH IT ALMOST
DIDN'T MATTER.
THEY WERE DOING EVERYTHING THEY
COULD THINK OF TO JUICE THE
STOCK PRICE.
THEY EVEN DID ONE OF THE BIGGEST
ONE-TIME DIVIDENDS IN MARKET
HISTORY AND THE STOCK YAWNED
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED TO STEVE'S
POINT, SOMEBODY HAD TO COME IN
AND SAY WHAT ARE OUR TRADITIONAL
STRENGTHS, HOW CAN WE KEEP THOSE
AND PLAY TO THAT STRENGTH?
BUT WHAT ARE ALL OF THE NEW
THINGS WE SHOULD BE DOING?
AND BALLMER IS ENTRENCHED.
HE CAN'T UNDUE SOME OF THE
PROJECTS THAT DIDN'T WORK.
IT'S THE REASON WHY YOU DON'T
LET A SURGEON FIX HIS OWN ERROR.
YOU NEED A NEW SURGEON TO COME
IN BECAUSE THE OTHER GUY WILL
LOOK AT THE SCALP INSIDE OF YOU,
NOT FIX THE PROBLEM.
THERE ARE OTHER STORIES LIKE IT.
I THINK DISNEY IS A GOOD
PARALLEL
STOCK COULD NOT GET OUT OF ITS
WAY AND ALL OF A SUDDEN THEY
NEED TO REINVENT THE ENTIRE
THING.
TO IGER'S CREDIT, HE DID NOT
NEED TO BE REPLACED BUT A FEW
YEARS IN THE TRENCHES TO GET TO
THE NEXT LEVEL
IN THE CASE OF MICROSOFT, THEY
DID NEED A NEW GUY.
>> THAT STOCK, BY THE WAY, WAS
$116 WHEN YOU TALKED ABOUT IT A
COUPLE WEEKS AGO, TO $132 AND
CHANGE.
>> YEAH.
EARNINGS ARE NOT GOING TO GROW
TO THAT EXTENT
IN FACT, THEY'RE GOING TO BURN A
LOT OF MONEY BUILDING THIS HOUSE
AND MARKETING IT AND DOING
PROGRAMMING.
THIS IS A RERATING
THIS IS PEOPLE SAYING IF I'M
PAYING 65% FOR NETFLIX, MAYBE
DISNEY SHOULDN'T BE 15 TIMES
>> IT'S ALSO SCARCITY.
THERE'S SCARCITY OF STORIES LIKE
THIS YOU CAN BUY, TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF OVER THE TOP.
AND THIS IS ONE.
>> TO YOUR POINT, MICROSOFT WAS
AT THE MERCY HOW MANY GRAY BOXES
PEOPLE WERE BUYING FROM COMPAQ
AND DELL
THAT WAS THEIR BUSINESS.
THEY HAD TO LIVE AND DIE ON THE
PC SALE CYCLE.
IS THIS THE UP CYCLE OR DOWN
CYCLE?
NOW THEY SELL DIRECT AND
SUBSCRIPTION MODEL, THEY DON'T
HAVE TO RELY ON PC SALES
DISNEY IS NO LONGER RELIANT ON
CABLE SYSTEMS.
THEY HAVE THEIR OWN DESTINY IN
THEIR OWN HANDS AND SELL OVER
THE TOP.
>> BALLMER WAS LOOKING
EXTERNALLY TO BUY YAHOO! AND
OTHER THINGS
NADELLA IS LOOKING INTERNALLY SO
YOU DON'T HAVE TO LIMIT ASSETS
AND THAT'S WHAT CHANGED.
>>> COMING UP -- A BIG WIN FOR
TWO HALFTIME REGULARS.
AND WE WILL GET AHEAD FOR THE
BIGGEST NEED FOR EARNINGS YET.
WE MENTIONED MORE THAN 100 S&P
COMPANIES REPORTING NEXT WEEK.
LERE ARE THE MARQUEE NAMES ON
THATIST.
WE WILL GO THROUGH THEM COMING
UN
♪♪
This is the family who booked
the flight,
who saved by adding a hotel,
which led to new adventures,
♪♪
that captured their
imaginations
♪♪
and turned moments into
memories.
With flights, hotels,
activities and more
for your Florida vacation,
Expedia has everything
you need to go.
You might take something
for your heart...
your joints...
or your digestion...
so why wouldn't you
take something
for the most important
part of you...
your brain.
With an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish,
Prevagen has been shown
in clinical trials
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
>>> HI, EVERYBODY, I'M BRIAN
SULLIVAN IN FOR TELLY TODAY.
WE WILL HAVE MORE ON THE IPO
BONANZA, WITH PINTEREST AND
ZOOM, STRONG DEBUT SO FAR.
WHERE DO THEY GO FROM HERE
WHAT DOES IT MEAN FOR THE NEXT
WAVE OF IPOs
>>> PLUS, WALL STREET BRUSHING
ASIDE THE MUELLER REPORT FOR
NOW.
WILL IT DERAIL ANY ATTEMPTS
GETTING NEW POLICY DWON P DONE
IN D.C.?
>>> AND SHOULD THEY CHANGE THE
LEGAL SMOKING AGE FROM 18 TO 21.
THAT'S WHAT IS BEING PROPOSED.
WE WILL TALK ABOUT THAT.
SEE YOU AT THE TOP OF THE HOUR.
>> LOOK FORWARD TO IT, BRIAN
>>> SHARES OF UNITED RENTALS ARE
HIGHER TODAY AND AFTER THE
COMPANY BEAT ON THE TOP AND
BOTTOM LINE, OUR STOCK, ONE OF
OUR VERY OWN STEVE WEISS HAS
BEEN BUYING THAT STOCK
GOOD DAY FOR YOU, CONGRATS.
>> THANKS.
AND STOCKS SELL CHEAP.
I WOULD LIKE TO BUY MORE IF IT
PULLS BACK
THE STORY HIRE IS THERE'S SOME
CONCERN BECAUSE WEATHER WAS SO
BAD IN THE FIRST QUARTER BUT THE
CEO CAME OUT AND I MENTIONED ON
AIR ABOUT A MONTH AGO SAYING
LOOK, IT'S NOT BOTHERING US,
WE'RE FINE
SO YOU HAVE A CEO ABLE TO MANAGE
THIS COMPANY EXTREMELY WELL,
NUMBER ONE RENTAL COMPANY IN THE
COUNTRY.
THEY'RE TIED TO THE ECONOMIC
SIGEL.
THEY'RE GETTING PRICE.
THEY'RE GETTING MORE
CONSTRUCTION
LOOK, I THINK YOU WANT TO OWN
THIS
THEY CAME OUT WITH THE PRICE
STARTING $160, THIS IS ONLY 5.2
TIMES, 20 EBID COMPANY.
>> KUDOS TO THE LINKSTER ALSO,
STEPHANIE LINK
THIS IS A NAME SHE'S TALKED
ABOUT A WHILE TOO.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THIS?
>> I THINK IT'S GOOD
I LIKE UNITED RENTALS.
HONEYWELL WAS A GREAT QUARTER.
YOU MENTIONED IT BEFORE.
BUT IT'S A CLASSIC EXAMPLE OF A
COMPANY TELLING A STORY GE IS
NOT TELLING.
8% ORGANIC GROWTH.
WHERE IS IT COMING FROM?
GE IN THAT BUSINESS?
I DON'T THINK SO
FANTASTIC QUARTER FOR HONEYWELL.
SPECIFIC TO THE COMPANY, STAY
WITH IT.
I THINK IT CONTINUES TO GO
HIGHER AND HIGHER.
>> LET'S GET AFTER EARNINGS NEXT
WEEK
BUSIEST WEEK FOR THE S&P,
COCA-COLA, FACEBOOK, CAT,
BOEING, AMAZON, EXXON -- AND
THAT'S JUST A SHORT LIST OF ALL
OF THE NAMES COMING OUT NEXT
WEEK
ONES THAT MATTER
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, YOU KNOW, I'M
LOOKING FOR THE FACEBOOK, RIGHT?
ALTHOUGH THE INTERESTING READ
THROUGH THAT SAYS BOEING AND A
CAT ARE GOING TO GIVE US NEXT
WEEK ARE INTERESTING
OUT OF MY OWN PORTFOLIO, I DON'T
EXPECT ANYTHING BUT GREAT THINGS
OUT OF THEM, AND TO HELP WITH
THE FANG NAMES, IF YOU WILL.
>> JOSH, ARE YOU GOING TO GET
IT
>> I THINK IT'S GOING TO SHIFT
FROM USER GROWTH, WHICH AT 2
BILLION IS IMPOSSIBLE.
I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED IF SOME
AROUND LIFTS START ASKING
QUESTIONS WHETHER INSTAGRAM
COULD SUSTAIN ANY MORE ADS
SO NOW THERE'S GOING TO BE THAT
CONVERSATION, LIKE HOW MUCH
BETTER CAN IT GET GIVEN THE USER
BASE, LET'S SAY THE USER BASE
SLOWS DON IN TERMS OF HOW BIG IT
GETS
>> HOW ABOUT THE LITTLE BLUE
BIRD.
>> THEY HAVE GAINED TRACTION
WITH ADVERTISERS THIS YEAR, THAT
SEEMS TO BE THE TONE, A LOT OF
OTHER PEOPLE ON WALL STREET SEEM
TO BELIEVE THAT AS WELL.
TWITTER IS LIKE THE ULTIMATE HIT
OR MISS EVERY TIME, THEY HAVE AN
INCREDIBLE QUARTER, THE NEXT
QUARTER COMPLETELY BLOW YOU UP,
THE QUARTER AFTER THAT, IT'S A
CLEAN SLATE, NOTHING EVER
HAPPENS MUCH THIS IS A TOUGH
NAME TO OWN IN THE EARNINGS,
THERE ARE VERY FEW OCCASIONS
WHERE YOU REGRETTED NOT OWNING
IT
THERE WERE MANY OCCASIONS WHERE
YOU WERE LIKE, I STUCK WITH IT
I AM HEARING ADVERTISERS ARE
HAPPY WITH TWITTER IN A WAY THEY
HAVEN'T BEEN IN THE PAST
>> A REFERENDUM ON THE GLOBAL
ECONOMY?
>> I'M NOT AS INTERESTED IN CAT
AS I AM BOEING
I BOUGHT SHARES YESTERDAY.
IT'S AS NEGATIVE AS YOU CAN
THINK ABOUT THIS QUARTER
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE HAD AIRLINES
COME OUT AND SAY, WE'RE NOT
PUTTING THE MAX BACK ON UNTIL
AUGUST
LATER, CANCELLATIONS, WHAT I
THINK IS GOING TO HAPPEN IS,
THEY'RE GOING TO BLEETH A SIGH
OF RELIEF AFTER THE QUARTER, NO
MATTER HOW BAD THE NEWS IS, IT'S
TEMPORARY, AND THE STOCK SHOULD.
IF THE MARKET'S GOING, THIS
STOCK IS GOING WITH IT
REGARDLESS
IN TERMS OF CATERPILLAR.
I BRING IT UP, BECAUSE REMEMBER
THE HIGH WATER MARK COMMENTS OF
MANY MONTHS AGO WHICH SORT OF
UPSET THE FEELING?
>> THIS COMPANY SEEMS TO PICK
CEO'S THAT DON'T KNOW HOW TO
COMMUNICATE WITH THE STREET.
YOU HAD DOUG OEBERMEYER.
WHO CAN MISS MORE QUARTERS OVER
A 3 TO 5 YEAR PERIOD, IT'S
ASTOUNDING
SO, YEAH, IT'S IMPORTANT IN
TERMS OF THE GROWTH AND SO
FORTH, WE GOT SOME UNITED
RENTALS.
THE QUESTION IS, RENT TO OWN,
THAT'S UNITED RENTALS.
>>> GASOLINE FUTURES ARE MAKING
A BIG MOVE INTO THE WEEKEND.
>> GASOLINE FUTURES SURGING INTO
THE LONG WEEKEND
NOW UP NEARLY 9%, LET'S BRING UP
OUR TRADERS.
WE'RE NOT EVEN AT PEAK DEMAND,
SO WHAT'S BEHIND THE MOVE?
>> I THINK IT'S LARGELY BECAUSE
OF REFINING CAPACITY, THIS TIME
OF YEAR, WE WOULD NORMALLY SEE
REFINERIES WORKING IN OVER 90%
RIGHT NOW.
A COUPLE REASONS IS, UNPLANNED
MAINTENANCE, THAT'S PART OF THE
PROBLEM.
THE TECHNICALS AND GRIZ IS GOING
TO TALK TO THE LEVELS.
THE CHART HAS BEEN FROM THE
LOWER LEFT TO THE UPPER RIGHT,
SINCE THE LOW IN STOCKS IN
DECEMBER
THE ONLY THING THAT THE BEARS
CAN HOPE FOR IS THAT IT
CONTINUES TO GET OVER BOUGHT
RIGHT NOW, IT IS OVER BOUGHT
WITH AN RSI OF 72.
>> GOT IT.
ANTHONY, HISTORICALLY THE PRICE
OF GAS RISES
IS THIS MOVE JUSTIFIED
>> YES, IT IS.
THERE'S REFINERY OUTAGES ACROSS
THE COUNTRY AND THAT'S HAVING A
RIPPLE EFFECT.
AFFECTING PRICES ALL OVER THE
U.S.
THE GOOD THING, THE GOOD NEWS IS
THAT WE'RE GOING TO HIT SOME
RESISTANCE IN THE MARKET RIGHT
NOW.
$3 IS PRETTY STRONG RESISTANCE
WE'RE NOT AT PEAK DEMAND
I STILL EXPECT PRICES TO GO UP,
BUT I DON'T EXPECT THEM TO GO UP
THE RATE THEY HAVE BEEN OVER THE
LAST FEW WEEKS
>> GENTLEMEN, THANK YOU.
>>> COMING UP ON OUR LIVE SHOW,
WE'RE JOINED BY JILL CARRIE
HALL, WHO WILL TELL US WHY A
STRONG IPO MARKET MAY BE A
BULLISH INDICATOR FOR THE
BROADER MARKET
PLUS, SHE'S CAUTIOUS ON THE
CHINA TURNAROUND, FUTURES NOW.
HALF TIME REPORT IS BACK IN TWO
MINUTES.
This is my headquarters.
This is where I trade and manage
my portfolio.
Since I added futures,
I have access to the oil markets
and gold markets.
Okay.
I'm plugged into equities -
trade confirmed
- and I have global access 24/7.
Meaning I can do what I need to
do,
then I can focus on what I want
to do.
Visit learnfuturestoday.com to
see
what adding futures can do for
you.
>>> WE'RE BACK, PINTEREST AND
ZOOM MAKING THEIR IPO'S TODAY.
>> I ALWAYS FOCUS ON HOW PEOPLE
USE THE PRODUCT FIRST.
WE'RE GOING TO FOCUS ON
CONTINUING TO GROW GLOBALLY, AND
OVER TIME, WE WANT PINTEREST TO
BE A GREAT PLACE FOR BUSINESSES
TO INSPIRE PEOPLE ON THE
PLATFORM
I WOULD FOCUS ON THOSE.
>> WE HAVE ZOOM, YOU CAN LIVE
ANYWHERE WITH ANY DEVICE, CAN
YOU TALK WITH THE CUSTOMERS AND
PARTNERS
>> WE ENDED WITH THE ZOOM CEO,
LET'S BEGIN OUR CONVERSATION
THERE.
JOSH BROWN
ZOOM IS THAT MOST UNUSUAL BEAST,
HE TWEETS, WHICH IS A PROFITABLE
IPO COMING OUT OF THE TECH
SECTOR
>> YEAH.
>> THIS IS A PROFITABLE COMPANY,
HENCE THE GINORMOUS POP.
>> THE PROFITS HELP, I ALSO
THINK DOUBLING REVENUE
AND THEN DOUBLING THAT FROM 18
TO 19, THAT IS VERY SPECIAL.
I ALSO THINK THE FACT THAT THIS
IS ENTERPRISE TECH RERVERSUS
CONSUMER SOCIAL MEDIA.
YOU ARE.
BUT THEY DON'T WANT THAT STIGMA
OF BEING -- EVERYONE WANTS TO BE
ENTERPRISE TAG, SOFTWARE
SERVICE.
THAT'S WHAT ZOOM IS, WE HAVE
USED THE PRODUCT INTERNALLY.
THESE ARE THE BEST COMPANIES ON
EARTH, RECURRING REVENUE IS THE
KEY.
>> THEY'RE EXPENSIVE, NO DOUBT
WHATEVER --
>> TEN TIMES SALES
THAT'S WHAT ALL THE PEERS TRADE
AT
>> YEAH, I THINK ZOOM -- I DON'T
THINK THE MARKET THINKS IT WAS
PRICED CHEAPLY, BUT YOU WANT TO
MAKE SURE IT WORKS
THERE'S ALWAYS MORE STOCK TO
COME, SO THEY DID THE SMART
THING, IT WILL BE A LOT TOUGHER
FOR LIFT TO DO A SECONDARY
GOING-FORWARD UNLESS THEY GET
THEIR STOCK GOING, I UNDERSTAND
IT
I THINK IT WAS WELL AIM LOCATED.
PINTEREST, IT'S A DIFFERENT
STORY, I'M NOT AS CHARGEDS UP
ABOUT IT AS I WAS WITH ZOOM.
I'M NOT IN EITHER IPO.
THAT'S GOING TO BE AN
INTERESTING ONE SEED
>> THEY'RE DOING THEIR BEST TO
MAKE YOU FORGET ABOUT WHAT HAS
BEEN A DISASTROUS POST IPO FOR
LYFT
>> YES
>> LET'S DO FINAL TRADES
>> DARDEN RESTAURANTS, I THINK
THAT ONE IS A GOOD ONE RIGHT
NOW, THEY'RE GOING TO CONTINUE
TO RAISE AND BEAT, IN IN THE
RESTAURANT SECTOR PER MY
ANALYST, WE'RE GOING WITH IT
>> KATE MOORE, ALWAYS GOOD TO
HAVE YOU HERE.
>> CONSUMERS, WHEN I'M