So why is space so important
to the automobile?
>> Hold on. This is major.
This is deep.
>> Well, it revolutionized
styling...
This looks like the thrusters
from a jet, coming out the back.
Modernized technology...
>> Now you've got a mean,
fighting machine.
>> And helped influence
some of the most expensive
and advanced machinery
in the world.
[window thuds]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
But as long as the unknown
is still out there,
space will continue to shape
our cars as well as our culture.
>> This is Space Age Americana,
right here.
>> This is the America I know.
>> Cheers, Jay.
- The best video game ever!
- [laughs]
- Tonight on
"Jay Leno's Garage"...
Yo!
Yeah, let's kill Jay.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
We're examining
the next generation
of all things automotive.
Let's face it, nobody makes
money selling last year's car.
How do vehicles evolve?
Ready to try and relive
some old memories?
- Yeah.
Do I have to take you along?
- And how can we
honor the past
while still moving forward?
- We had to make sure that
this car was everything
that it needed to be to win
a historic race like Le Mans.
- Tonight we'll see if
the next generation really
is the best generation.
Remember, you're never
too old to fall down.
Aah!
I get to be one of the first
people to get their hands
on Ford's amazing
new race-winning Ford GT.
I'll get you a check
as--in a couple of weeks.
Don't worry about it.
Legendary newsman
and former NSX owner
Ted Koppel gets the latest
scoop on the new Acura NSX.
This is 3.5 liter.
- Right.
- It's 575 horsepower.
- I love it when
you talk dirty to me.
- I'll check out the next
in a line
of powerful race bikes.
The acceleration
of this thing is really good.
And how bizarre is this,
a car that can be anything
you want it to be?
- The Blackbird truly is
the next generation
of car advertising.
- And Alonzo Bodden and I try
to teach an old-style bike
some new tricks
when we go off-road racing...
- This is insane.
- Emphasis on the "off."
[groans]
- You okay, Jay?
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Well, this episode is all
about the next generation,
'cause let's face it,
nobody makes money
selling last year's car.
You got to innovate, you got to
come up with new ideas.
The car I'm driving right now
is my 2005 Ford GT,
serial number 12.
That means the 12th car built.
The first ten cars
went to the Ford family.
The 11th car
was auctioned for charity,
and this is the very first
customer-delivered Ford GT.
This is the re-creation
of the car that won
Le Mans back in the '60s.
You know, Ford took on Ferrari.
It's a legendary story,
and won Le Mans,
so they tried to reimagine what
the car would look like in 2005,
and they developed this car,
which is true to the original,
and now,
they're gonna do it again.
Ford is back with the next
generation of the Ford GT.
I've been dying to
get my hands on one of these
ever since we got
a sneak peek at the prototype,
which tragically was not
road-ready at that time.
I think this car
just surprised everybody.
- There's even a lot
of employees in the company
that didn't know
we were doing it.
- Wow.
- And it was just as much
a surprise to them.
- And then they took
the new Ford GT
to Le Mans 50 years after
their first legendary victory,
and they won it again.
You know, when America can
build a supercar that competes
with the rest of the world,
it's really exciting.
Now,
after two very long years,
I'm on the way to get
my new Ford GT
and drive it
for the very first time.
♪ ♪
This is Dave Pericak.
He's head of global performance
for Ford Motor Company?
- That's correct.
- And my new Ford GT
is in the trailer.
I'm gonna see it
for the first time,
just like you are right now,
so this is pretty exciting.
- Are you ready to see it?
- I am ready to see it.
Let's take a look.
♪ ♪
Wow.
Looks fantastic.
♪ ♪
- Mr. Leno, your car.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Did you get the keys from him?
- I didn't get the--
he took the keys.
- Oh.
Yeah...yeah,
give Dave the key.
- Give them to me.
- Here you go, right there.
- There we go.
Jay, your new Ford GT.
- Well, thank you very much.
- Congratulations, sir.
- I'll get you a check as--
in a couple of weeks.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, it's pretty amazing.
Yeah, it just looks great.
- This was designed, you know,
to celebrate our heritage
and to celebrate
what's all behind the GT,
and at the same time we had
to make sure that this car
was everything that
it needed to be
to win a historic race
like Le Mans.
- You know what's great
about it is,
it's an actual racecar
for the street.
I mean, a lot of people
use that term,
but this was designed for
track first, street second,
and it's all aerodynamics.
That's really the key
to this car.
- Oh, this whole car's
about aerodynamics.
- I mean, you can literally see
how the air goes through it,
through up here, it cuts through
here, this is amazing.
- Well, you know what a lot
of people don't know, Jay?
This is not just beautiful, this
wing, but it's also functional.
- Like me.
- [laughs]
So the air is coming in.
- Right.
- And it's going through the
turbo, and it's getting cooled,
but then that charged air
is coming up through here,
actually through this piece,
and feeding the motor.
- Okay.
- And it's all been made
to increase downforce,
reduce drag,
and make this quick.
She achieves a top speed,
Jay, of 216 miles an hour.
- Wow, that's faster than
many, many supercars.
- It is, actually.
The McLaren does 205,
is what they've stated.
- Right, right.
- The Ferrari 458
does 205 as well.
- So if I'm on the 405 with this
and the McLaren is going 205,
I can easily pass them.
- You can easily pass them.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it's practical.
- You've been known to get up
to that speed on the 405.
- It's practical.
Honey, we can get to your
mom's house much quicker.
Let me tell you something,
it's really a privilege
to have one of these
'cause this is not
an easy car to get.
This is probably the first time
in the history
of the motor company
that it had to be
preapproved to get a car.
- We had roughly 6,800
applicants for 500 cars,
so the demand was high,
but we wanted to make sure
that this ended up
in the hands of people
who were gonna do
the right thing with the car.
- Right.
- We don't want people
to buy it and flip it.
- Right, right.
- You know, we don't want people
just to put them
in--in a museum somewhere.
We want them out on the street.
- Right.
- We want people to take them
to car shows, so yeah,
the application process
was--was very lengthy.
- Oh, and the number
of celebrities that called me,
"Leno, can you get--get me
on that list!
Why aren't I on that l--"
just furious that
they weren't on the list,
and I said,
"Well, you know, your Lambo
and your Ferrari's
not gonna help you here."
- Yeah, exactly.
We want to reward the people
that have been loyal
to Ford, and that's...
- Thank you.
- There you go.
- Since the first day
I rolled my mom's Falcon,
I have been there,
you know what I'm saying?
Very cool.
All right, enough talking.
Let's drive this thing.
[engine turns over]
[engine revving]
- Rotate that dial
to track mode.
- Track mode?
You get right there, don't you?
- You're hunkered down,
and you're ready to go out
and attack the track.
The grip is unbelievable.
You keep thinking you're gonna
slide, but you don't slide.
- No, you do not.
This thing just pulls like
a freight train, doesn't it?
- It really does.
- This feels like a racecar.
- I was gonna say, it's as
comfortable as a road car.
- Yes.
- I feel like
we're doing one of those
Doublemint--
it's two mints in one!
- [laughs]
- This is so smooth
and seamless.
- As soon as you hit
the throttle,
it's instantaneous torque.
It's not some big event
that happens,
but you're rocketing off.
That V-6 is an angry
little motor back there
giving you that power.
- Anybody who thinks
they're gonna miss the V-8,
you're gonna be
pleasantly surprised.
- Well,
speaking of surprises, Jay.
- What do you got?
♪ ♪
- Oh, yeah!
Wow, how cool is that?
Joey is a professional
racecar driver for Ford,
and that's one
of their actual racecars.
How cool is that?
♪ ♪
- You're not gonna let him
beat you, are you, Jay?
♪ ♪
The best video game ever!
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
- [chuckles]
Well, how cool was that?
- Was that all you had, boys?
- Yeah, that's all we got,
yeah, yeah.
- That's all we got.
- I'm carrying 150 pounds
of dead weight here.
- Yeah, yeah, he's--
- Yeah.
All right, let's be honest.
Even without Dave in the car,
there's no way
I could beat Joey.
Back in 2011,
he drove for BMW and won
Sebring and Daytona, and he's
one of the winning drivers
that drove the Ford GT
at Le Mans.
Well, I like the name Joey Hand.
Sounds like an old mob guy.
- That's right.
- Mickey the Snake,
Louie the Foot, Joey the Hand.
- Joey the Hand.
- Joey the Hand, hey,
Joey the Hand's driving Le Mans.
Hey, well, congratulations.
You've had a great career.
Is that--that seems like it
would be the highlight. Is it?
- It is, yeah.
That's a big one.
I mean, Le Mans really
is a different race.
It's a very fast track.
It's wet and dark.
I mean, there's so many things
that can go against you.
In the GTLM class we were racing
each other the whole time.
- Yeah.
- I mean, I passed the Ferrari
at the beginning of the race,
and I passed the Ferrari for the
last time with four hours to go,
and everything
in between was a race.
It was--it was no cruising,
so I mean, that race,
it just--it's one that makes
your eyes pop out of your head.
It's like driving
I-5 in the fog.
- Right.
- That's what I tell everybody.
- Now,
this is not the car that won.
This is obviously a racecar.
- Right, this is not
the one that won,
but I actually have
the car that won.
♪ ♪
This is the car, Jay.
- Wow.
- This is the one that won.
- Actual French dirt
and everything.
- This is French dirt.
- French bugs.
- Yeah.
- French everything.
- You know, a lot of factors
go into winning
a race like Le Mans.
Obviously
you need a great car,
but it's just as important
to put together
the perfect team of drivers,
mechanics, and support people.
- It's quite a process to--
to choose your drivers,
and we were being approached
by agents, the drivers.
everybody wanted to be
a part of the program.
You know,
you also got three drivers
driving this car together
for 24 hours.
They have to click as well.
- Here's a dumb question.
They're not driving together.
You get out of the car,
another guy gets in.
- Right.
- The integration is what?
- Oh, well, I'll let the driver
tell you that.
- Just from the steering
position, the seat.
- Oh, okay.
- You've got a guy
that likes the car really loose
and a guy that likes the car
with a lot of understeer.
- Right.
- That's not good for both,
right?
So you got to learn
to compromise,
and lucky Dirk Muller,
one of my teammates,
we raced together for years.
We knew each other
already coming in.
You know, then we had
Sebastien Bourdais,
and he was kind of
our French connection.
- You got to have a French guy.
- Right.
And he's won a lot
of championships in IndyCar,
really good wheelman.
- And I guarantee
the French are gonna say,
"Bourdais is the winner
of the race,"
and you two guys are back here.
"He is the Frenchman.
He's won the race."
- That's the way it was.
The week before the race you do
a big autogra--a parade,
and you sign autographs.
It was just Bourdais.
- Right, yeah.
- He's from Le Mans.
He was born in Le Mans.
- Oh, well, there you go.
- So it was Bourdais
and the American and the German.
- Yeah, yeah.
Well, congratulations, Joe.
I mean, it's an amazing
accomplishment.
Now for the ultimate
dumb question...
Can we take this one for a ride?
- Not this one, Jay, not this
one, but I'll tell you what.
If you want--and you'll be the
only guy that's ever done this,
you want to drive the one
that Joey was just driving?
- Can I do that?
- You can do that.
- Cool.
- Get your other foot in there.
Hold on.
There you go.
- All right, that's about as
good as I'm gonna get in there.
- You can give me your wallet.
There you go.
- I don't trust
any of you [bleep].
[laughter]
[engine turns over]
[giggles]
Fantastic!
I got to get me one of these!
Oh, I got one already!
I forgot about that!
Yes!
Coming up...
Perestroika, my friend.
- [laughs]
- The Russian's strength
versus motocross track.
- Jay Leno has lost his mind.
- And somehow,
I wind up the loser.
[groans]
- You okay, Jay?
We got no free pass.
Everything we have,
we've earned.
The unmistakable Lexus IS.
Lease the 2019 IS 300 for
$329 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
I like to make my life easy.
( ♪♪ )
Romo mode.
(Beep)
(Bang)
Good luck
with that one.
Yes!
That's why I wear
Skechers Slip-Ons.
They're effortless.
Just slip them
right on and off.
Skechers
Slip-Ons,
with
Air-Cooled
Memory Foam.
♪ LiMu Emu & Doug ♪
Mmm, exactly!
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay
for what you need.
Nice! But uh, what's
up with your partner?
Oh! We just spend all
day telling everyone
how we customize
car insurance
because no two
people are alike, so...
LiMu gets a little
confused when he sees
another bird that
looks exactly like him.
Ya... He'll figure it out.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
- This episode is all about
the next generation,
so, of course, we started off
with a high-speed racecar.
The best video game ever!
- [laughs]
- But the next generation
isn't always about technology.
Sometimes you can go forward
while going backward.
I'm with my old friend,
fellow motorcyclist,
and comedian Alonzo Bodden.
- Nothing like a nice getaway
in the beautiful brown hills
surrounding Los Angeles.
- You've seen Alonzo
on this show before.
Not too long ago he kicked
my buttocks on the flat track
when I had
a dislocated shoulder.
- I liked how Alonzo ran up
the inside there
and pushed you wide.
That's a standard dirt track
move right there.
- But now I've got
a relocated shoulder,
and I'm ready
to kick his butt.
Alonzo likes
the fast Japanese bikes,
but I want to see what he thinks
of this old-school technology
that's been updated.
- Can't wait to try to pick up
a date with this rig.
- This is called a Ural.
Now, if you've never heard
of one of these, well,
that's 'cause
it was built in Russia.
Actually,
this whole motorcycle
is a copy
of a World War II design.
These were popular because
they had two-wheel drive,
meaning the sidecar
was also a drive wheel,
and that extra traction made
them great for off-roading
through snow, mud,
and just about anything else.
So you say to yourself, "Okay,
the name of this episode is
'The Next Generation.'"
Well, that's what this is.
This is the next generation
of one of these Ural bikes.
It's basically old technology,
but it's been upgraded with
Brembo brakes, fuel injection.
It's really kind of a perfect
mix of retro and modern.
Now, this is my personal bike,
but we borrowed one for Alonzo,
and it's his first time riding.
- How come Laurence Fishburne
gets to go on a racetrack
in the BMW,
and I get to go on
a dirt road in a Ural?
I got to make some movies.
- Perestroika, my friend.
- [laughs]
- What do you think?
- I hate to admit it,
because
if I tell you this is fun,
I don't know what
you're gonna put me on next.
- But you know,
so many of the bikes
it's just about
going crazy fast,
where this is the only
motorcycle I've seen
that only goes to 100.
- I think if you could do 100
on this thing,
you could win something.
[laughs]
- Let's see how
it does on this track.
- He's got to be kidding.
We're not actually going on
a motocross track on this thing?
Jay Leno has lost his mind.
- These Urals are great
at off-roading,
but that's a very,
very different thing
from a motocross track.
See,
motocross bikes are designed
to be fast and nimble,
while these Urals are designed
to stay on the ground,
slow and steady.
Take a curve too fast
on one of these,
they'll tip over on you,
but that's what makes it fun,
right?
- This is insane.
[laughs]
This is the first time
I've considered
riding a motorcycle
an act of faith.
- What's on the other--yo!
Boy, you feel like
this thing's gonna tip over.
- [laughs]
- Your natural instincts
are completely different
than a normal motorcycle.
[both laughing]
- I don't know
if I've ever laughed
this much going this slow.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
[dramatic music]
Yo!
♪ ♪
[groans]
- You okay, Jay?
You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
- All right.
[engine turns over]
- There we go.
These things are heavy, crude,
but indestructible, like me.
Yee-haw!
- We are cooking now.
I'm doing well over
ten miles an hour.
- You kind of steer it
with the throttle
a little bit to bring it around.
I know I almost flipped
this thing a minute ago,
but I'm feeling confident now,
and that means I'm gonna
make this competitive.
Oh, man these--these things
are a lot of fun, aren't they?
- Man, this is a blast as long
as you don't flip over
and kill yourself.
- No, that's all right.
- [laughs]
- You know something?
There are those that
just follow the chosen path,
and there are those who choose
to make their own path
through life.
I saw the road not taken,
and I made it a road.
- The road less traveled?
- That's right.
- It's less traveled
for a reason, Jay.
- That's right, that's right.
- [laughs]
- You know what we should--
let's try hill climbing.
- All right.
- Let's see
who can bring the
other guy up the hill fastest.
- All right.
[bird caws]
Ready, Jay?
One, two, three, go.
♪ ♪
- Whoa!
- There you go, there you go,
there you go, come on, come on,
come on, we can make it,
we can make it, we can make it!
Done.
20:53.
- A lot of wheel spin.
- Yeah.
Any tips?
- No, I don't know
what I was doing.
- [laughs]
- I would start it.
- Think so?
[engine turns over]
- Ready, set, go.
♪ ♪
Very good, wow,
now, much better, very good.
♪ ♪
Oh, I got 18 seconds.
- Now,
that's how you climb a hill.
I think you had more
dead weight in the side car.
- Well, that's--that's true,
but so far you've beaten me
every time on motorcycles.
I got to keep having you
on the show until I beat you.
- It's job security, Jay.
- Job security.
- [laughs]
- Good job, Alonzo, my friend.
- This was great, man.
This was great.
- Built like Russian bull,
strong.
- Yeah, yeah,
whatever you just said.
- Now let's take a look
at the vehicle
that's revolutionizing
the way cars are filmed.
In fact, you've probably
seen it already.
You just didn't know it.
- The Blackbird truly is
the next generation
of car advertising.
My name's Pete King.
I'm an executive producer
at the Mill here in Los Angeles.
- The Mill is
a visual effects company
known for their CG work,
and one of their specialties:
car commercials.
- Nowadays
cars are almost exclusively
designed in the computer,
so there wouldn't be a physical
vehicle to actually film,
and when you're making
a commercial,
it's pretty hard to do it
without an actual car,
so before the Blackbird
we did it in kind of
the old school way,
which was to take
a previous year model,
put a bunch of tracking
markers on it to
then replace it with the render
of the actual vehicle in post.
We thought there had to be
a better way to do it.
- They realized that
as long as
you have the right wheel base
and performance,
you can digitally
put any car body on top,
and it'll look real.
- It can be adjusted
for length and width.
It's got an electric engine
that can be programmed
to mimic the acceleration
curves and performance
of virtually any automobile.
For filmmakers,
the Blackbird really gives
a lot of flexibility
because you can create whatever
you want over the top of it.
We use those cool-looking
graphics on the outside
to track it in real time.
It allows the director or the DP
to actually see their render
over the Blackbird
as they're filming in the real
lighting it's in at that moment.
This is groundbreaking
technology.
This thing is
working constantly,
and we're actually having
to build more of them this year.
We're gonna have them in Europe.
We're gonna have them in Asia.
We're gonna have them
in the east coast of the U.S.
It's gonna be working
all the time.
- When we return...
You know, a man in your position
should be driving
an automobile like this.
We'll see how
veteran newsman Ted Koppel
reacts to the new NSX.
- Damn, that's a lot of power.
-Guys, I want you
to meet someone.
This is Jamie.
You're going to be seeing
a lot more of him now.
-I'm not calling him "Dad."
-Oh, n-no.
-Look, [Sighs] I get it.
Some new guy comes in
helping your mom bundle and save
with Progressive,
but hey,
we're all in this together.
Right, champ?
-I'm getting more nuggets.
-How about some carrots?
You don't want
to ruin your dinner.
-You're not my dad!
-That's fair.
Overstepped.
When I book at Hilton.com
I get to select my room
from the floor plan...
Free Wi-Fi...
...and the Price
Match Guarantee.
So with Hilton
there is no catch.
Yeah the only catch
is I'm never leaving.
No I'm serious,
I live here now.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
♪ I'm tasting olives... ♪
♪ Roasted pine nuts... ♪
Book at Hilton.com
♪ Mmm this red pepper... ♪
♪ That's spicy stuff... ♪
Fresh flavor. Feel good food.
Sabra Hummus.
♪ I just had Sabra Hummus and
now I feel good! ♪
I had a heart problem.
I was told to begin my
Aspirin regimen,
and I just didn't listen.
Until I almost lost my life.
My doctors again ordered
me to take Aspirin,
and I do.
Be sure to talk to your doctor
before you begin an
Aspirin regimen.
Listen to the doctor.
Take it seriously.
"Curiouser and
curiouser,"
said Alice.
“The rabbit-hole
went straight on
like a tunnel for some way.”
"I've seen a cat without a gri,
but a grin without a cat.”
Hey, Mercedes, end audio.
Change lighting to soft blue.
The completely reimagined
2020 GLE.
With intelligent voice control
and available third row.
Your adventure awaits at the
Mercedes-Benz Spring Event
but hurry the event
ends April 30th.
[upbeat music]
- The car I'm driving right now
is a 2017 Acura NSX,
all-wheel drive, hybrid, fast.
In fact, with the demise
of the 918 Porsche,
this is the fastest
hybrid car you can buy.
Amazing automobile,
it really is an incredible car,
but this is the next
generation of the NSX.
When Honda first came out
with an NSX in 1990,
it was revolutionary.
It was the only
mass-produced car
to feature
advanced aerodynamics,
titanium connecting rods,
and an all-aluminum body,
which made the NSX the first
high-performance supercar
with the comfort
and reliability
of an everyday driver.
Supercars prior to that
were somewhat unreliable.
People just accepted the fact
that supercars were quirky
and needed constant tune-ups,
and it's all part
of the ownership process,
but Honda really set a standard
for every company
from Ferrari to Lamborghini
about how to build a supercar.
I tracked down a guy who had one
and was passionate about it,
sold it,
and has regretted it ever since,
and I'm gonna let him
drive this one
and find out how this new one
compares to the old one.
♪ ♪
Ted, how are you?
- Jay, I thought this hotel
catered to a better
class of people.
- Apparently not.
- Apparently not, right?
- If anything,
he belongs here,
and I certainly do not.
See, this is Ted Koppel.
He anchored "Nightline"
for over 25 years,
and he's one of
the most respected
broadcast journalists
this country has ever seen.
Now, Ted, as a big motorcycle
enthusiast, you had a BMW?
- I had a BMW 1100R.
- Right.
- Nice bike.
- Very nice bike.
- My wife made me get rid of it.
- Really?
- Yeah, she--yes, afraid so.
- Oh, man.
- Well, you know, there--
there comes a point
after you've reached your
appointed threescore and ten...
- Right, right.
- When it's not too smart
to get out there
on a bike anymore.
- Oh, I'll keep that in mind.
- Oh, you do that.
- Yeah, I--I still like
to ride, actually.
- Of course you do.
Of course you do.
- Yeah, I still like to ride.
- You're a crazy man.
- Luckily, your wife hasn't told
me not to ride, so I'm okay.
- No, but she's gonna
call your wife.
- Oh, yeah, now, don't do that.
Don't do that.
But you're also a big car guy
'cause I remember
you were an NSX guy.
- I had an NSX from '97
until about 2014,
so I had it for a long time.
- Okay, okay.
- Yeah.
- Well, I'll tell you what.
I've got the brand-new NSX
here today.
- You're kidding.
- I want to get
your opinion on that.
- You're--you just pay me
the normal fee.
You don't have to give me a car,
for crying out loud.
- No, no,
I'm not giving you the car.
- Oh.
- I just want you to drive it
and see what you think,
and I've got--
from the Honda Museum,
I've brought one
of the original NSXs,
one of the first generation
ones,
and I'd like you to drive that
one just to refresh your memory.
Then we'll put you
in the new one
and get your impression from
the newsman's point of view.
♪ ♪
- That is one pretty little car.
- That is a '91 NSX.
This is the very first
generation car.
Pretty clean design.
- This is a gorgeous car.
- Well, you ready to try
and relive some old memories?
- Yeah, do I have to
take you along or can I--
- Yeah, I'm sorry,
that's quite--legally,
you have to take me.
I was thinking the same thing,
but hey,
this is what we got to do.
[chuckles]
[engine turns over]
- Oh, yeah, that's nice.
- Bring back some memories when
you step on that accelerator?
- Oh, that's lovely.
This is a nice-handling car.
It still is.
- Now, when you got your NSX,
did you realize
the importance of it?
- I hate to admit that
in front of this many cameras
next to my old friend
Jay Leno, but no, not at first.
I was a body man.
I just loved
the look of the car.
- You know, even though
we were late-night rivals,
I always liked Ted.
In fact, one time
I invited him on my show.
I remember once
you rode a motorcycle
on "The Tonight Show."
- That's very true.
I rode the bike onto the set,
thereby enhancing my image
as a rebel.
- Yeah.
In the early days
I was up against Johnny.
It didn't change much,
frankly, you or Johnny.
Both of you
beat the crap out of us.
- Yeah, but you were
doing important stuff.
- In many ways
I feel like Forrest Gump
because I was with Mandela
when he came out of prison.
I was in the Kremlin
with Gorbachev
the day the Soviet Union ended.
- Wow, actually, Gorbachev
told me a very funny story,
which is, there was
a line of people in Russia,
and they'd been
waiting hours for bread,
and one Russian said,
"I hate this line.
You know what I want to do?
I want to kill Gorbachev."
Hey,
and everybody in the line...
Three hours later,
the guy comes back.
They said, "What happened?
You kill Gorbachev?"
He said, "No, that line
was longer than this one."
[both laughing]
I thought that was
a pretty good joke.
- That's not bad.
- Well, for a communist,
come on.
- Yeah, not bad.
Do you remember
the old John Wayne story?
He had this agent
by the name of Manny,
and periodically they'd go out,
they'd have four or five beers.
- Right.
- John Wayne would go
to the bathroom,
and he'd come back,
and there'd always
be the same thing,
his white trouser leg
soaking wet.
After about 20 years of this,
Manny's never asked him
about it before,
and he's--he can't stand it.
He says,
"Duke, what happens in there?"
"Well, I'll tell you, Manny.
"It's always
the same damn thing.
"I'll go in there, some dude'll
stand at the urinal next to me,
"all of a sudden he looks up,
and he says, 'Jesus Christ,
you're John Wayne.'
- Oh, and he pees all over him?
- I was hired to do an interview
with Bill Clinton,
and I tell that story,
and then I turn to Clinton
and say, "That must happen
to you all the time,"
and he says, "Yeah, except in
my case they do it on purpose."
- [laughing]
Oh, that's funny.
That's a funny story.
Now, would you rather drive this
or your Porsche Boxster?
- Hmm.
I love that Porsche Boxster,
but this--this car
is very special.
- This one does it for you.
- This one does it for me, yeah.
And it makes me kind of wonder
whether I did the right thing.
- Well, it's not too late
to go back and find another one.
- That's true, yeah.
♪ ♪
And we are ready.
Well, that was fun.
I enjoyed it.
- Yeah, yeah, brought back
some memories, huh?
- It did.
- Obviously,
Ted loved his original NSX,
but the second generation
is really a great car.
- It's very blue, isn't it?
It's--
- It is blue.
- It's very blue.
- It shouldn't take too much
to make Ted a true believer.
What's it gonna take?
You know, a man in your position
should be driving
an automobile like this.
- You're right.
- Let's put you behind the seat
and show you what it feels like.
- There we go.
Now you're talking.
[engine turns over]
- Let me tell you
what we have here.
The other was a 3-liter
and 276 horsepower.
- Yeah.
- This is 3.5-liter
with 575 horsepower.
- I love it when
you talk dirty to me.
- And--now, the other was
a two-wheel drive,
rear-wheel drive only.
This is a all-wheel drive car,
and you've got
an electrically-driven motor,
as well, so it's a hybrid.
- Well, I mean, when you buy
a $200,000 car,
you worry a lot about
the price of gasoline, right?
- Well, yeah.
- I know the people who buy
this car are just thinking,
"Man, if I can save a few bucks
by going electric."
Damn, that's a lot of power.
- Feels good, doesn't it?
See, you got to have
one of these now.
- No, I don't.
- I can see that look
in your eye.
- No--for real,
it was a kick driving it, but...
- No, no, no?
Well, I guess
I should have realized
Ted's love
for that original NSX
is hard to replicate.
He's an old-school guy.
Now, are you one of those guys,
nobody drives your cars?
Have you let anybody else
drive your NSX?
- I-I once let
one of my daughters drive it,
and some other guy.
Oh, yeah, Colin Powell.
- Oh, Colin Powell?
Oh,
Colin Powell's a real car guy.
- I know he is.
I drove over in the NSX,
and he said,
"Do you mind if I drive it?"
I said, "Of course not."
So he hops in, he peels out.
He gets about 1/4 mile
up the road,
and I hear--boom--
this huge explosion.
One of the tires had blown.
He brings it back on the rim,
gets out of the car,
and he's laughing.
He says, "You know, Koppel,
it's still a federal crime
to try to kill a sitting
Secretary of State," so...
- [laughs]
That's funny.
Well, Ted, thanks so much
for taking the time to do this.
It's really been fun.
- Oh, it's been a great delight.
You've always been someone
whose career I've enjoyed
and whom I've enjoyed knowing
as a friend.
- You're one of the few guests
I enjoy talking to as much
off-camera as on-camera.
- Thank you.
Same here.
- Coming up,
one of the fastest racetracks
in the world
with one of the fastest
motorcycles in the world
with an old guy on it.
Yeah, let's kill Jay.
Yeah, that's an idea.
What could go wrong there?
♪♪
[elevator bell]
Yup.
Little choices make
a big difference.
Like delicious fruits
and veggies.
However You Healthy.
Naked.
I had a heart problem.
I was told to begin my
Aspirin regimen,
and I just didn't listen.
Until I almost lost my life.
My doctors again ordered
me to take Aspirin,
and I do.
Be sure to talk to your doctor
before you begin an
Aspirin regimen.
Listen to the doctor.
Take it seriously.
Opening doors with Cologuard.
Turning 50 opens the
door to a lot of new things...
like now your doctor may be
talking to you
about screening
for colon cancer.
Luckily there's me,
Cologuard.
The noninvasive test
you use at home.
It all starts when your
doctor orders me.
Then it's as easy
as Get, Go, Gone.
You get me when I'm
delivered...
right to your front door
and in the privacy of your
own home.
There's no prep or
special diet needed.
You just go to the bathroom,
to collect your sample.
After that, I'm gone,
shipped to the lab for
DNA testing
that finds colon cancer
and precancer.
Cologuard is not right for
everyone.
It is not for high risk
individuals,
including those with a history
of colon cancer or precancer.
IBD, certain hereditary
cancer syndromes,
or a family history
of colon cancer.
Maybe I'll be at
your door soon!
Ask your doctor if
Cologuard is right for you.
Covered by Medicare
and most major insurers.
GLAD YOU'RE BACK
HOW YOU FEELING?
♪ ♪ ♪
(BOTH) EXHAUSTED.
BUT FINALLY BEING ABLE TO MAKE
THAT VOLUNTEER TRIP HAPPEN
WAS... AWESOME.
AWESOME.
YOU HAVE TO SCRUB.
WHAT DO THEY...
THEY USE FOR WASHING.
♪ ♪ ♪
LET'S DO IT EVERY YEAR.
WE'LL DO IT EVERY YEAR.
I THOUGHT YOU'D SAY THAT -
LET'S DO IT.
♪ ♪ ♪
SEE HOW INVESTING WITH A J.P.
MORGAN ADVISOR CAN HELP YOU.
VISIT YOUR LOCAL CHASE BRANCH.
Great. Another wireless ad.
So many of them are full of this
complicated,
tricky language about their
network and offers
and blah blah blah blah blah
blah.
Look Sprint's gonna do things
differently,
and let you decide for yourself.
They're offering a new 100%
Total Satisfaction Guarantee.
Try it out and see the savings.
If you don't love it, get your
money back.
See? Simple.
Now Sprint's Unlimited Plan
comes with one of the newest
phones
included for just $35 a month.
So switch now.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- I'm in Texas visiting
some old friends of mine.
That's right, we're back
at Revival Cycles in Austin.
♪ ♪
Hey, Alan, hi, Stefan.
How are you guys?
- Great.
Welcome back.
- Remember we were here
last year?
We had the wall of death.
[cheering]
How do you not get dizzy?
These guys are bike obsessed,
from the oldest
of the old school
to the most
cutting-edge technology.
And what do you got over here?
- Well...
- Today they've gotten ahold
of something brand-new,
and they're gonna
let me ride it!
- This is the 2017 Suzuki
GSX-R1000.
- Now, I've got
the older version of this.
I think mine's a 2008.
- Oh, man, the technology that
they've added to this bike
is just a landslide
from the last generation.
- See, when I bought my other
one, "Oh, it's unbelievable.
It's never gonna
get better than this."
"Oh, that old thing.
Well, we got the new update."
What does this have?
- They call it a base model,
but it's still a extremely
advanced motorcycle.
This has variable valve timing.
It's got ride-by-wire throttles.
It is unbelievable
what this thing has.
- Hold on.
The most important part,
it has 200 horsepower.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, I mean,
that's pretty amazing.
- Yeah.
- It's a faster machine.
- And, of course,
this is the base model,
and then they got the R model.
- The R model has picked up
even further on the advancements
from the base model.
They've really made this kind
of unruly beast of a machine
with so much raw power
as docile as a kitten,
so we're pretty convinced
that we could take this
to a racetrack
and have you go at it
for a track day.
- Well, I've never actually been
on a racetrack with bike.
You want to give it that shot?
Is that something
you're suggesting?
- Yeah, I think
that's the whole idea.
- Yeah, let's kill Jay.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
- Let's kill Jay today.
- Hey, cool.
[rock music]
♪ ♪
The Circuit of the Americas,
or COTA, as it's called,
is a 20-turn
counterclockwise track
with a 133-foot
elevation change.
In other words,
it is really challenging.
So I called in
a professional,
one of the designers
of this track,
who happens to be a pretty
good motorcyclist himself.
- Kevin.
- Good job, guys.
- Yeah, I am not worthy,
first of all.
Kevin Schwantz is
a motorcycle racing legend.
This 1993 world champ has had
25 grand prix victories,
and the fact
that an amateur like me
is gonna share the track
with him
shows you just how stupid
television can be.
- It's amazing what a great job
Suzuki's done
with this new bike.
It's been a while
since they had a new GSX-R1000,
but they definitely
did their homework.
I just got back from the tough
duty of being at Magello
and riding these GSX-Rs
up the front straightaway
at 295 kilometers an hour
as you make
that last little rise,
and it lifts the front wheel.
- Yeah.
- And that's when you know
you're a man.
- I was like, what.
- Okay, well,
that's not gonna happen today.
- Not today, yeah.
- No, that's not gonna happen
today, Kevin.
- So we're gonna start you off,
Jay, on the standard model,
finish you up on the R model,
which hopefully we'll notice
quite a difference
in what you feel and what
you notice about the motorcycle.
- Yeah, I'm curious to see
if I can tell the difference.
He can run over a dime and tell
you whether it's head or tails.
I'm going,
"What's wrong with this bike?"
"Oh, you got a flat tire."
"Oh."
- Oh, oh, yeah.
- Yeah, I mean, that's...yeah.
- All right, well, we're gonna
time you on the base model.
- Oh, don't time me.
It'll be--
- We want to see what happens.
- Does it go in hours?
Really, guys?
- We won't tell you what it is.
- Yeah.
- We're just gonna time you,
and then as you step up,
we'll see the difference that
it might make in your times.
- Let's give it a shot.
[engines revving]
Okay, I'm just trying to do
what--what Kevin does.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Let the bike run out
just a bit wide,
pulling it back nice and tight
on the exit to set up
for this tricky little downhill
left-hander at turn seven.
- Now, you see, he just
falls into the corners.
Meanwhile, I'm going wide
on every corner here.
Oh, man.
[chuckles]
He is so far ahead of me.
- Up on two minutes now.
I wonder what Jay's
thinking right now.
"Don't fall off.
Don't fall off."
- Aah!
Remember, you're never too old
to fall down.
I mean, the acceleration
and the pulling power
of this thing is really good.
You know, I still think
my 2008 is a great bike,
but this one is
a perfect example
of the next generation
being an improvement
in practically every way...
and this is just
the base model.
I can't even imagine
how the R model's gonna feel.
The amazing thing about these
motorcycles is, you get Ferrari,
Lamborghini,
McLaren-type performance
for literally
pennies on the dollar.
- Oh, hell yeah.
- Hey, they're carrying
pretty good speed.
- [bleep] yeah.
- So what was the time?
- We've got a base lap of 4:23.
- Ooh.
- You know,
being right behind Kevin,
I don't think I've ever focused
on another man's rear end
as much as I did.
- You were working that joke up
the whole time, weren't you?
- Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean,
this is an amazing machine.
Braking is unbelievable.
I'm used to riding older bikes
where slowing is a suggestion
as opposed to actual braking.
- Let's up the ante
a little bit.
Let's get you
up to the next bike
and go out there
and see what you can do.
♪ ♪
- So what makes this
a next generation model?
First off, they've added
a bunch of
advanced rider aides,
a launch control system
that gets you going faster,
a more sophisticated
front fork and rear shock,
and an IMU-influenced motion
track antilock brake system,
which is another way of saying
this bike will kind of
smooth out any dumb mistakes
that you make.
The more miles
you put on this thing,
the more confident you get.
- Yeah, here they come.
3:32--that's, like,
a 50-second difference.
- A huge improvement.
- Okay, man,
I'm getting sick
of watching them.
Let's go join them.
♪ ♪
- You know, you get out
on a track on a motorcycle
and you realize
how brave these guys are.
♪ ♪
Well, that's a lot of fun.
This makes, like,
a bad rider okay,
an okay rider pretty good,
and a good rider
probably excellent.
- That's pretty incredible
to ride a modern bike
on a track for the first time.
- Well, I wanted to wait
till I was 67 before I did it.
I just wanted to have
the maturity to go with it.
- To be mature.
- You were making sure
that you enjoyed it.
- Yeah, yeah, exactly.
- Well, there was a big
difference in your lap times
between the standard bike
and the R model.
- Yeah?
- Something like 50 seconds,
really--yeah.
- Really?
- That's an eternity
on the track.
- You know,
I did stop and get a burger.
- Oh, that's why.
- That might explain.
[laughter]
Coming up,
we go behind the bow tie...
- There is a little chip out of
the bottom of the spoiler here.
- I thought I liked him.
- And find out
how to appraise a car
that's practically brand-new.
- If it were my car, it'd have
more than 454 miles on it.
- I don't like Donald anymore.
- [laughs]
So, you're open all day,
every day.
That's what 24/7 means, sugar.
Kind of like how you
get 24/7 access
to licensed agents with GEICO.
Hmm?
Yeah, you just go online,
or give them a call anytime.
You don't say.
Yep. Now what will it take
to get 24/7 access
to that lemon meringue pie?
PIE!
PIE'S COMING!
That's what it takes, baby.
GEICO®. Great service
from licensed agents, 24/7.
AI unlocks the art of science.
When you open a bottle of beer,
I don't think many people
actually know
the level of science
that's filled into that bottle.
Back in time, it took Carlsberg
several years
to produce a new beer.
But using
Microsoft Artificial
Intelligence,
we will be able to detect
new flavors in a split second
and develop better beers
faster.
With AI, we redefine
what's possible.
So cheers!
When you book at Hilton.com,
you get the Price
Match Guarantee.
So if you find your
room at a lower rate,
Hilton is like...
We're gonna match that rate
and give you an extra 25% off.
What would travel sites do if
you found a different price?
That's not my problem,
it's your problem.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
We switched.
I switched.
I switched
to Chevy.
I switched to Chevy.
We switched to Chevy.
We switched for value.
For family.
For power.
It was time to upgrade.
I switched from Ram to Chevy.
See why people are
switching to Chevy.
We love our Chevy.
I love my
Malibu.
My Colorado.
My Camaro.
My Traverse.
Why did we switch?
Just look at it.
♪♪
When you rent from National...
it's kind of like playing your
own version of best ball.
Just look at it.
Because here, you can choose any
car in the aisle,
even if it's a better car class
than the one you reserved.
So no matter what,
you're guaranteed to have a
perfect drive.
[LAUGHTER]
(VO) Go National. Go Like a Pro.
See what I did there?
[lively music]
- Buckle up, folks,
it's time to assess and caress
with Donald Osborne.
♪ ♪
- ♪ If you love
classic cars ♪
♪ Then Donald loves you ♪
- You all know Donald Osborne,
our appraiser extraordinaire.
This episode, we want to learn
about appraising a modern car.
What goes into that?
This is a 2008 Dodge Viper ACR,
correct?
- Yes, this is a car
that is practically new,
so what I'm looking for is,
what exactly is the story
that it's telling us?
ACR stands for
American Club Racer.
This is a Viper for the track.
- Right, and this was, I think,
the first year
of the ACR, correct, 2008?
- It was the first year
of the ACR, limited edition car,
and cars like this,
high-performance,
late-model cars are frequently
valued in the market
by their mileage
or lack thereof.
- All right, well,
let's bring the owner in.
His name is Jeff Dunham,
a very funny comedian.
Jeff plays clubs and theaters
all across the country.
- How are you, Jay?
Good to see you.
Donald, good to see you.
- Hey, good to see you.
- Did you buy this
as a collector car?
Did you buy it just
as a fun car for the road?
Did you buy it as a track car?
What was your reason?
- It was all of the above,
actually,
and you don't know this,
but working
the Comedy Magic Club
down in Hermosa Beach,
you brought your '93 Viper
there,
and that's when
I fell in love with Vipers.
- Oh, that's right.
You were just four years old,
as I remember.
- That's right.
- I remember picking up
a young buy
and the policeman saying,
"Put him down."
That was you.
- That was me.
- Yeah, yeah.
- So, the Dodge Viper,
the '94 was actually
the first really nice car
that I bought,
and this thing came up for sale,
and I'd never had an ACR
and thought this sounded
like a lot of fun.
This car's sticker price
was 102,000,
and I paid 85,000 for it.
- You had the '94,
and then you buy sort of
a race version of your '94.
- Right.
- Do you notice
a huge difference on the street?
- This is completely different.
- Really?
- Because this isn't just
an ACR.
This is the hardcore ACR,
so this 80 pounds lighter
than the coupe.
This thing is a monster
all the time.
- Well, the first thing
I noticed, of course,
as we discussed
about low-mileage cars,
this car has 454 miles on
the odometer when I examined it.
- 454 miles?
Is your wife still a virgin?
- [laughs]
- So,
this is how I look at any car
that I appraise.
You look at basic things.
For instance, you obviously
start with the body.
The panel fit
is actually very good.
The panel condition
is excellent,
and considering
the way it's built,
I'm very surprised that
there's not more damage,
but there is a little chip
out of the bottom
of the spoiler here,
which I'm sure, Jeff,
at some point,
caught the edge
of a driveway somewhere.
- You know,
this is why many appraisers
are often beaten to death.
- And those are called
rub strips.
You're supposed to rub them.
- Absolutely, they're actually
designed to bolt in
and bolt out very easily
so you can replace those.
- Now, if this was your car,
would you replace it
because of that little chip?
- Absolutely not.
In fact, if it were my car,
it'd have more than
454 miles on it.
But the car has been used.
There's a small scratch
here on the sill.
Someone getting in scraped their
heel, and there's a slight--
- Excuse me, excuse me.
- Yeah, sir?
- Hold on a second.
- Let the record show
that that did not
actually cover the scratch,
and--but I noticed
on the chassis
there's some light road dust,
as well as a dead moth
on the radiator.
- I thought--
- You know, you are so screwed.
- I thought I liked him.
I don't like Donald anymore.
- But things like this are
the challenges of appraising
a basically new car because I am
picking the tiniest of nits.
- Right, couldn't you do this
to the moth, really,
and that would be pretty much
the end of the problem?
- I'm not allowed to intervene.
I observe.
- So if the car was on fire,
you wouldn't pick up
an extinguisher?
- I would make a note.
- That's just--
- Okay.
- Oh, my lord.
- Are you curious to hear
his appraisal of this?
- Can I make a guess?
- You certainly can.
- Yeah, go ahead.
- I'm gonna guess that
it's gonna go for about what
I paid for it, 85,000, 90,000.
- What do you think, Jay?
- It might go for 105,000.
- Okay, so...
- This and more after a brief
message from our sponsors.
For more cool cars, go to
jaylenosgarage.cnbc.com.
Is that for me?
Mhm
Aaaah!
Nooooo...
Quick, the Quicker Picker Upper!
Bounty picks up messes quicker
and is 2x more absorbent than
the leading ordinary brand.
(Son loudly clears throat)
(Mom and dad laugh)
Bounty, the Quicker Picker
Upper.
On a budget? Try Bounty
Essentials.
♪ I'm tasting olives... ♪
♪ Roasted pine nuts... ♪
♪ Mmm this red pepper... ♪
♪ That's spicy stuff... ♪
Fresh flavor. Feel good food.
Sabra Hummus.
♪ I just had Sabra Hummus and
now I feel good! ♪
After walking six miles at
an amusement park...
Bill's back needed a
vacation from his vacation.
So he stepped on the
Dr. Scholl's kiosk.
It recommends our best
Custom Fit Orthotic
to relieve foot, knee, or
lower back pain.
So you can move more.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to move.
Don't tell your mother.
Dad, it's fine.
We have ALLSTATE.
AND WITH CLAIMRATEGUARD
THEY WON'T RAISE YOUR RATES
JUST BECAUSE OF A CLAIM.
That's why you're my favorite...
I KNOW.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
♪
With the Capital One Savor Card
you earn 4% cash back on dining
and 4% on entertainment.
So when you go out, you cash in.
What's In Your Wallet?
♪
At Hilton.com,
I can choose from all their
different hotel brands...
Like a DoubleTree
for my cousins.
A Homewood Suites
for my uncle.
A Hampton for
my sister and her kids.
And the Waldorf Astoria
Beverly Hills for me.
Can I get a..?
Thank you.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
Really?
[horn honks]
Man this is what I feel like
when I wear regular shoes,
cramped and uncomfortable.
We can arrange a little upgrade.
Which is why I wear Skechers...
Wide Fit shoes.
They have extra room throughout.
They're like a luxury
ride for my feet.
Try Skechers
Wide Fit shoes.
I have a vision
correction number,
But I'm more than a number.
When I'm not sharing ideas
with my colleagues
I'm defending my kingdom.
My Essilor lenses offer more
than vision correction
with three innovative
technologies
For my ultimate in vision
Clarity
And Protection
Together in a single lens:
The Essilor Ultimate
Lens Package.
So, I can do more
of what I love!
Buy two pairs of
Essilor's best lenses
and get a $100 back instantly.
See more. Do more. Essilor
- And we're back
with Donald Osborne.
- Here we have Jeff's
2008 Dodge Viper ACR.
Five years ago,
interestingly enough,
they sold for about $123,000
'cause people wanted them.
- Right.
- Wow.
- Today, the same car sells
for about 105,000.
However, because we are speaking
specifically of this car
with its 454 miles
and owned by a car guy...
- Right.
- Provenance comes into effect.
This car would be $155,000.
- Wow.
- Donald, thank you.
I was really, really curious,
so this was fun.
- Thanks so much, Jeff, really
loved looking at your car.
- Thank you.
- But let's take it for a ride.
- All right.
- Let's put a--
- And you're driving?
- Let's put a quick
1,500 miles on there.
[laughter]
You know,
I was expecting, really,
to be a noisy slam-bang car.
It's actually comfortable,
plenty of room, plenty of power.
- Well, this is a car guy's car.
- Yeah.
- And I think that's why
guys that get them
do appreciate them.
- Jeff, I think you should
take this car out
and put 100,000 miles on it.
[both laughing]
I got to get me one of these!
Oh, I got one already!
So, is the next generation
the best generation?
Depends on who you ask.
- If I tell you this is fun,
I don't know what
you're gonna put me on next.
- The power of nostalgia
is real.
Bring back some memories when
you step on that accelerator?
- Oh, that's lovely.
- But one thing's for sure.
The better the technology,
the safer we all are.
[groans]
- You okay, Jay?