>> FINAL TIP, ABOUT HALF A
MINUTE LEFT BEFORE WE'LL HAND IT
OVER TO "SQUAWK ON THE STREET.
TURN AROUND STRONG ECONOMIC
DATA
UP 2.3 ON THE S&P 500, NASDAQ
DOWN 3
MARKET OPENS THE SAME TIME THAT
THE PRESS CONFERENCE STARTS, I
THINK.
DOESN'T IT
>> YES.
>> YES
RIGHT AT 9:30 A.M.
IS NEWSY A WORD?
IT'S GOING TO BE A NEWSY DAY.
>> VERY NEWSY DAY.
IPOs, POT STUFF, BARR STUFF.
>> JOIN US ON MONDAY
"SQUAWK ON THE STREET" IS NEXT
I DID IT
>> GOOD THURSDAY MORNING
WELCOME TO "SQUAWK ON STREET."
I'M CARL QUINTANILLA ALONG WITH
JIM CRAMER, DAVID FABIAN
PRESS CONFERENCE IN ABOUT HALF
HOUR
FUTURES HAVE GONE POSITIVE
EUROPE IS HIGHER DESPITE LITTLE
IMPROVEMENT IN THEIR PMIs, BUT
AWFULLY GOOD DATA HERE
BEST NUMBERS SINCE 2017.
WE BEGIN WITH THE IPO WAVE AFTER
L
LYFT'S STUMBLE.
>> PLUS MUELLER'S MOMENT
ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR WILL
ADDRESS REPORTERS THIS HOUR
BEFORE RELEASING THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S FINDINGS ON THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN AND RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE IN THE 2016
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION.
>>> AND RETAIL SALES SURGING IN
MARCH.
FASTEST PACE IN NEARLY TWO
YEARS.
STOCKS ARE SET FOR A GREEN OPEN.
>>> A PAIR OF UNICORNS ARE
LAUNCHING THEMSELVES IN THE
PUBLIC MARKET TODAY.
PINTEREST BEGINNING TRADE,
PRICING $2 ABOVE THE HIGH-END OF
THE RANGE AT 19.
ZOOM VIDEO COMMUNICATIONS
GETTING READY TO GO PUBLIC AT
THE NASDAQ, PRICING 36 THIS
YEAR, VALUING THAT COMPANY AT
MORE THAN $10 BILLION.
WE'LL TALK TO CEOs OF BOTH
PINTEREST AND ZOOM ONCE THEY
BEGIN TRADING, JIM
BOTH PRICING ABOVE THE RANGE,
ALTHOUGH LYFT, AS WE SAID --
PINTEREST BELOW THEIR PRIOR
ROUND.
>> RIGHT
ZOOM HAS INCREDIBLE GROWTH
130, 1%, 116%.
IT'S PROFITABLE.
GUYS THAT LEFT FROM WEB X, CISCO
BOUGHT THEM.
THERE IS A SENSE THAT THESE GUYS
ARE VERY MUCH THE HOT IPO FOR
BIG TECH FOR THE YEAR.
I WANT PEOPLE TO KNOW IT'S GOING
TO OPEN -- IT OPENS WHERE YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT AT 14 TIMES SALES
AND THAT IS HUMUNGOUS.
PEOPLE SHOULD KNOW IT'S VERY
EXPENSIVE.
IT HAS GREAT GROWTH.
REPORTED LAST NIGHT, PEOPLE
REPORTED, CLOSEST ANALOG AND 20
TIMES SALES.
LET'S BE CAREFUL
PINTEREST IS A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
11 TIMES 2019 SALES IF IT OPENS
WHERE IT IS AND EIGHT TIMES FOR
NEXT YEAR.
NOTICE WHAT I SAID
TIMES SALES NOT TIMES EARNINGS
PINTEREST SHOULD BE PROFITABLE
NEXT YEAR.
I GUESS WHAT I'M SAYING IS THAT
THESE STOCKS ARE ALL EXPENSIVE.
>> THEY ARE, BUT THEY'RE ALSO
GROWING VERY QUICKLY.
>> YES.
>> YOU LOOK AT ZOOM'S NUMBERS,
WHICH IS PROFITABLE, SLIGHTLY.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT A
COMPANY WHOSE REVENUE WAS 60.8
MILLION, 151 MILLION AND 30
MILLION.
>> IT'S BIG.
>> FISCAL YEAR THAT ENDED 2019
OR JANUARY 31st, '19
THEY ARE GENERATING CASH, TO
YOUR POINT, IT'S OBVIOUSLY
TRADING AT A VERY HIGH MULTIPLE
TO BOTH REVENUES.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND THE LITTLE EARNINGS THEY
HAVE.
>> I THINK THERE'S ENOUGH
BUSINESS THAT WEB-X, CISCO WILL
NOT CRUSH THEM
I USE THE PRODUCT.
>> THE ZOOM PRODUCT?
>> YES.
>> IT'S A SUBSCRIPTION BASED
VIDEO CONFERENCING
>> FOR A PERSON, ORGANIZATION,
ALL SORTS OF DIFFERENT WAYS?
>> LET'S SAY YOU WANTED TO DO AN
ONLINE PRESENTATION AND YOU
WANTED TO HAVE DIFFERENT PEOPLE
TALKING, YOU JUST USE ZOOM
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO.
>> IT'S WORKING.
PEOPLE ARE VERY EXCITED ABOUT
IT
PINTEREST, THEY'RE EXCITED ABOUT
IT, BECAUSE IT'S BELOW WHERE
THESE OTHER GUYS BOUGHT IT
WOW, I'M GETTING IN BELOW.
I'M GOING TO GO BUY CAMEL?
NO
REALLY SMART PEOPLE PAY HIGHER
SO WE FEEL LIKE WE'RE GETTING A
BARGAIN.
>> DO YOU HAVE A PREFERENCE IN
THESE TWO TODAY?
>> IF IT OPENED BELOW 50, I
WOULD BE DISAPPOINTED.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT --
>> IN THE LATE ROUNDS?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, PINTEREST IS ONE
THAT PEOPLE ARE GOING TO SAY I
FINALLY HAVE ANOTHER ONLINE PLAY
BESIDES FACEBOOK AND TWITTER
THAT'S HOW PEOPLE VIEW IT.
THEY WANT IT ONLINE PLAY.
>> THEY NEED TO OWN IT, YOU
FEEL, IN ORDER TO HAVE EXPOSURE,
TO SOME EXTENT
>> YES.
>> IT'S NOT ABOUT SHARING.
>> RIGHT
IT'S ABOUT CARING, NOT SHARING
SEE, MARK ZUCKERBERG SHARES
EVERYTHING WITH THE RUSSIANS AND
ANYBODY ELSE
THESE GUYS ARE CARING.
IT'S NOT SHARING, IT'S CARING.
PINTEREST CARES.
>> CUTTING THEIR LOSSES IN HALF
DOESN'T LAST YEAR DOESN'T HURT.
>> NO.
LOOK, THEY OBVIOUSLY KNOW HOW TO
RUN A COMPANY.
LOOK, VERSUS SNAP, IT IS
ACTUALLY THE SAME.
SNAP DOWNGRADED TODAY.
IT IS THE SAME PRICE OF SALES
FOR '20 VERSUS SNAP.
TWITTER IS CHEAPER
I THINK TWITTER IS DOING WELL
AND TWITTER IS CHEAPER
IF YOU LIKE PINTEREST,
THEORETICALLY, YOU SHOULD LOVE
TWITTER.
THINK ABOUT THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN OKAY SF THIS
IS FIRST CLASS ANALYSIS.
>> I DO NOT DOUBT THAT IT IS.
>> NOBODY HAS THIS ANALYSIS.
>> NO ONE?
>> NO.
AT LEAST WE DID IT OURSELVES.
>> TWITTER, YOU MENTIONED
TWITTER.
IT WAS AT 75 COMING OUT OF THE
GATE.
>> THERE'S A PAY TOO MUCH,
RIGHT?
THAT WAS A PAY TOO MUCH
SITUATION.
>> SNAP.
>> SNAP DID, TOO
REMEMBER, IT'S THE INDUSTRIALS
THAT PEOPLE WANT RIGHT NOW
YOU MEAN SPECIFICALLY THE GREAT
NUMBER
>> HONEY WELL RAISING THEIR
GUIDE.
UNITED RENTALS REITERATING THEIR
THE YEAR IS UNFOLDING JUST LIKE
THEY THOUGHT.
>> THEY RAISED THE RENTAL RATES.
THAT'S WHAT WE WERE WAITING FOR.
THIS IS GOING TO BE SO STRONG.
ONE OF THE THINGS THAT I THINK
FACEBOOK IS SO WRONG, THIS HAS
PICKED UP BIG IN MARCH AND
APRIL.
I DON'T WANT TO GET INTO A FIGHT
WITH VARIOUS PEOPLE.
>> WHAT ABOUT PAPER STOCKS
>> TOO MUCH CAPACITY IN PAPERS
BECAUSE THOSE -- I MEAN, SOME OF
THOSE PEOPLE THEY KEPT OPENING
FACTORIES, EXPECTING THAT THINGS
WILL BE GREAT.
AMAZON CARDBOARD AND THEY WERE
THINKING OUT OF PLASTIC INTO
PAPER.
IT'S JUST STRAWS
INTERMODAL
IF YOU GO TO THE CSX, THEY'RE
GOING TO TELL YOU THAT WE'RE
DELIVERING THINGS ON TIME IN THE
RAILS.
>> NOT AS MUCH AS INVENTORY
AS --
>> TRUCKING ALSO --
>> A MARKET SHARE ISSUE?
>> INTERMODAL.
HOW MANY --
>> WE KNOW.
>> 1800 CONTAINERS ON A
CONTAINER SHIP, OKAY
>> YES.
>> WE STOPPED BECAUSE OF THE
TARIFFS.
WE DID REALLY BIG.
WE LOADED UP, TOOK ALL THE STUFF
IN, BETTING THAT THE TARIFFS
WOULD GO UP.
WE WERE FULL UP AND THAT WAS THE
END.
IT HAD TO DO WITH THE TARIFFS,
DAVID.
>> DEUTSCH DOES CUT JP TO A
SELL.
>> WHERE WAS HE YESTERDAY?
IT DOESN'T EVEN MATTER
THE COMPANY'S CONFERENCE CALL
WAS SO HORRIBLE.
JANUARY WAS BAD, FEBRUARY WAS
BAD, MARCH WAS BAD
IT WAS 767 IN TERMS OF DECLINES.
THAT WAS ONE OF THOSE COMP CALLS
WE SAID THE FED IS SO RIGHT.
THEN ON HONEYWELL, WOW, IS THE
FED WRONG.
SISTER, MOTHER, SISTER, MOTHER.
>> CSX, RAILS MATTER
CONTINENTAL WAS VERY GOOD.
>> RIGHT.
>> NOW THERE'S A LOT OF THEM
THAT ARE REALLY GOOD
HOW ABOUT INTELL DOING
COMPLETELY BADLY AND IT GOES UP
TWO POINTS?
NOW YOU HAVE A 2020 NUMBER
DO YOU KNOW THAT THOSE MODEMS
WEREN'T GOING TO BE READY UNTIL
2021 AND THEY WERE GOING TO MISS
CHRISTMAS AT APPLE
NOW WE HAVE NOT A REFRESH BUT AN
ENTIRE NEW CYCLE
5G IS GOING TO BE SO BIG.
>> BIG.
>> SO BIG.
>> WHAT'S THE BEST 5G PLAY
YOU HAVE TO DO IT IN THE FORM OF
A QUESTION
WHAT IS ERICCSON.
>> REALLY?
>> I'M NOT KIDDING
WHO ARE THEY WINNING
UNITED STATES.
WHO ARE THEY TAKING THE SHARE
FROM
CAN'T HEAR YOU
I'M NOT LISTENING.
HUAWEI
WHO IS THAT?
I'M NOT LISTENING.
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
>> NO.
I REALLY DON'T
I SIT HERE AND I DO NOTHING.
>> BACK TO THE IPOs.
BOB PISANI WILL HAVE A BUSY DAY
ON THE FLOOR WATCHING ALL THAT
ACTION
GOOD MORNING, BOB.
>> GOOD MORNING, CARL.
CNBC IS INSIDE THE BOOTH
GLENN PERELL WILL BE THE
DESIGNATED MARKET MAKER, HANDLE
A LOT OF IPOs, TWITTER, ALIBABA.
WHERE IS EVERYBODY BEHIND HIM?
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO SEE A CROWD.
THEY'RE ALL UPSTAIRS
THERE'S A BREAKFAST MEETING
GOING ON, NYC HOLDS A BREAKFAST
MEETING FOR EXECUTIVES OF THE
NEW COMPANY.
GLENN GOT HERE A COUPLE OF
MOMENTS AGO.
BIG DAY DOWN HERE.
WE HAVE THE UPSIZE FROM
PINTEREST FROM $19 TO $15 TO
$17.
MORE THAN THAT
WE HAVE THREE -- NOT ONE, NOT
TWO, BUT THREE UP SIZE IPOS ON
THE NASDAQ, ZOOM, $36.
TALK THERE WAS 28 TO 32.
THEY'RE IN OIL AND GAS MINERAL
COMPANY.
AGAIN THEY UPSIZE.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS THIS.
IPOS MARKET IS COMING OUT OF THE
GATE VERY, VERY STRONG RIGHT
NOW.
LYFT IS A LITTLE BIT OF THE
OUTLIER.
JUST THE LAST TWO OR THREE WEEKS
LOOK AT JUMIA, PAGERDUTY, TUFIN
SOFTWARE, LEVI STRAUSS, THEY'RE
ALL COMING OUT OF THE GATE VERY
STRONG
LEVI STRAUSS, 38
LYFT DOWN 17%.
THAT'S THE OUTLIER
IS IT THE RIGHT PRICE FOR
LYFT -- EXCUSE ME, FOR THIS
PARTICULAR IPO FOR PINTEREST
LYFT WAS 50% ABOVE THE LAST
ROUND OF FUNDING
PINTEREST.
FINAL NUMBER LOOKS CLOSER TO
THAT
ALL I CAN TELL YOU IS THAT THERE
SEEMS TO BE INTENSE DEMAND
WE'LL BE STANDING HERE 9:30
TOMORROW, IN THE NEXT HALF HOUR,
GIVE YOU AN UPDATE AND MAYBE GET
EARLY INDICATIONS.
I DON'T EXPECT THIS TO BE COMING
AT 10:00 A.M. EASTERN TIME
PINTEREST IS SO HIGH IT'S GOING
TO TAKE A WHILE TO BUILD THAT
BOOK AND WE'LL EXPLAIN THAT MORE
AT 9:30.
GOLDMAN IS THE LEAD BOOK RUNNER,
CONSULTING WITH GTS, DOWN HERE
BUILDING THAT BOOK
I ANTICIPATE THAT WILL BE SOME
TIME PAST 10:30 AT LEAST
WE'LL HERE, NEXT HALF HOUR WITH
AN UPDATE.
BACK TO YOU.
>> BOB PISANI, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH
I THINK WE HAVE SOME
CONFIRMATION ON CANOPY ACREAGE
IS THAT WHAT'S CROSSING?
>> YES
CANOPY IN CANADA, ACREAGE IN
AMERICA.
NETWORK OF STORES, GOOD COMBO.
>> PAY ATTENTION TO THAT DEAL.
VERY BIG IN THE SPACE.
RAPID CONSOLIDATION.
>> YES, CONSOLATION GAVE THESE
GUYS $4 BILLION, BRUCE LITTON
AND SAID HERE IS THE BALL.
BRUCE LITTON SAID I AM GOING TO
MAKE MY STOCK BIGGER THAN YOUR
STOCK.
IMAGINE THAT
BRUCE LITTON
DO YOU REMEMBER THE OLD DAYS
>> YES.
>> HE'S BACK, BIGGER THAN EVER
VERY GOOD MERGER
THEY'RE TRYING TO LOCK THEM UP
HATS OFF TO MELISSA.
SHE HAS BOTH OF THEM.
>> ACREAGE IN AMERICA AND THE
OTHER LARGELY CANADA
>> HE HAS NEVER EVEN INHALED
THOSE JUULETTES, BE CAREFUL, WE
KILL YOU
WE'RE GOOD FOR YOU
SEE THOSE?
>> WE'LL TALK TO THE CEO'S OF
PINTEREST AND ZOOM AS SOON AS
THEIR STOCKS START TO TRADE.
ATTORNEY GENERAL WILLIAM BARR IS
PREPARED TO GIVE A PRESS
CONFERENCE IN 15 MINUTES AS THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT PREPARES TO
RELEASE THE MUELLER REPORT
WE'LL TAKE YOU THERE LIVE AS
SOON AS IT BEGINS.
RETAIL SALES, CLAIMS, FED COMING
BACK IN WITH HIGH EXPECTATIONS
WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT
It all comes down
to a single defining moment...
...when a plan stops being a
plan and gets set into motion.
Today's Merrill
can help you get there
with the people, tools,
and personalized advice
to help turn your ambitions
into action.
What would you like
the power to do?
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
What do all these people
have in common, LiMu?
[ guttural grunt ]
Exactly. Nothing!
They're completely
different people.
That's why they
make customized
car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need.
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done it again, LiMu.
[ LiMu grunts ]
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
>>> SHARES OF BLACKSTONE WAY UP
THIS MORNING, REPORTING RESULTS
THAT IT WILL SHIFT FROM A
PARTNERSHIP TO A CORPORATE
STRUCTURE.
>> WE CAN SELL TO 4.5 TRILLION
TO 12.
IF WE MAKE THIS CHANGE TO BE A
CORPORATION, LIKE EVERY OTHER
CORPORATION, THEN WE CAN DOUBLE
THE NUMBER OF PEOPLE
WE STILL HAVE A FEW LEFT WHO
CAN'T.
I THINK THAT WILL CHANGE OVER
TIME.
>> IT WILL ALLOW INTERNATIONAL
AND DOMESTIC INVESTORS TO INVEST
EASIER.
>> THIS IS SOMETHING THEY TALKED
ABOUT, MADE AN IMPRESSION ON
KKR DID IT, THE STOCKS HAVE
BENEFITED.
THIS IS A QUESTION I'VE ASKED A
NUMBER OF TIMES.
THEY'VE PERFORMED VERY WELL FOR
THEIR INVESTORS YET THE STOCK
PRICE HAS NOT PERFORMED
PARTICULARLY WELL OVERALL, NOT
REFLECTING IN SOME WAYS THE
SUCCESS OF THE UNDERIING
BUSINESSES
IT'S MORE OR LESS TRACK THE S&P
AND THIS HAS BEEN A FRUSTRATION
FOR THEM
IT'S A BELIEF THAT THIS DISCOUNT
THEY TRADE AT, 36% DISCOUNT WILL
DISAPPEAR IN TERMS OF BECOMING A
C-CORP
6.2% YIELD.
>> THE TWO HARDEST PLACES TO GET
JOBS ARE BLACKSTONE AND GOLDMAN
SACHS AND THE TWO WORST TRADING
STOCKS ARE BLACKSTONE AND
GOLDMAN SACHS.
WHERE THE YOUNG, SMART PEOPLE
ARE TRYING TO GO AND WHERE THE
MONCY TRYING TO GO
I THINK IT WILL BRING AN
AFFIRMATIVE WHEEL.
>> 88 BILLION UNDER MANAGEMENT
UNBELIEVABLE
HE WAS ASKED ABOUT THE MARKET
AND SAID, QUOTE, IT'S BEEN A
GOOD YEAR THAT WE'VE HAD A RUN
YEAR WITH THE NASDAQ UP ALMOST
THEN HE HAD POLICY PRESCRIPTIONS
ON INEQUALITY.
>> RIGHT.
>> HAVING THE MINIMUM WAGE GO UP
AND HAVING SCHOOL TEACHERS PAY
NO TAX, WHICH GOT ATTENTION.
>> HE HAS BEEN A GIGANTIC GIVER
TO THE SCHOOL DISTRICT THAT
JERRY SEINFELD IS FROM
HE'S TRYING TO MAKE A
DIFFERENCE
WHAT CAN I SAY
I DON'T THINK HE'S BEING
SOCIALIST.
I DON'T THINK HE'S BEING HARD
RIGHT.
JAMIE DIMON MIGHT POSSIBLY --
ANY CHANCE OF SUCCESS THERE WITH
MARIANNE LAKE?
>> IMPORTANT MOVE THERE
YESTERDAY.
YOU NEED ANOTHER GENERATION THAT
CONCEIVABLY CAN TAKE OVER AT
SOME POINT
HOW MANY GENERAL RAGS HAVE WE
GONE THROUGH AS WE TALK ABOUT
SUCCESSION OF JAMIE DIMON?
AT LEAST THE THIRD.
>> YEAH.
WE'VE GOT BIG BANK EARNINGS,
BB & T, SUNTRUST GOOD NUMBERS
BUT JP MORGAN IS UP 10
I HAVE NO IDEA HOW SOMEONE COULD
DOWNGRADE THAT RIGHT NOW
NOTHING IS AS BAD AS THE --
>> I THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING TO
SAY GOLDMAN PEPSI.
>> YES
HOW DID YOU KNOW
>> PEPSI TO NEUTRAL AFTER ALL
THIS TIME.
>> THAT WAS AN ILL-ADVISED SELL.
THAT WAS ONE OF THE GREAT
CONFERENCE CALLS OF ALL TIME.
>> ANOTHER ONE, REALLY
>> A REALLY GREAT ONE.
>> THE MOUNTAIN DEW YOU DRINK
WHEN YOU'RE GAMING, WHAT IS
THAT, ROCKET FUEL, THAT MUSK
USED ON THAT FALCON?
>> COULD BE.
>> DOESN'T HAVE SUGAR, ALCOHOL
IT'S OCTANE 93.
>> WE'LL GET TO CRAMER'S MAD
DASH
WE'LL TAKE A LOOK AT THIS BEFORE
MARKET OPEN, BEFORE THE
PINTEREST AND ZOOM OPEN AND
BEFORE THE BARR PRESSER.
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
At CDW we get that modernizing
your IT infrastructure
requires deep thought.
So quite staring out the window
and give CDW a call.
They will assess your
infrastructure needs,
then design and implement
a modernization solution
using fast HPE gen-10 servers
with security features
built into the hardware.
And provide Hewlett
Packard Enterprise
Proactive care services,  24/7
monitoring and support
to keep your infrastructure
agile, healthy and reliable.
For modernized IT Infrastructure
you need Hewlett
Packard Enterprise
and IT orchestration by CDW.
[knocking]
♪
Memories.
What we deliver by delivering.
>>> THERE'S A LOOK AT PINTEREST,
MAKING THEIR PRESENCE KNOWN.
ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR ON THE
MULLER REPORT AS IT MAKES ITS
WAY TO THE PUBLIC.
WE THINK SOMEWHERE IN THE 11:00
HOUR IT WILL BE DELIVERED TO THE
PUBLIC AND CONGRESS ON CD-RANGE
OF MOTIONS
CD-ROMS.
SO THEY'RE MAKING SURE THEY HAVE
COMPUTERS THAT OPERATE CD-ROMS
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT SAYS
LIGHTLY REDACTED AND A GRANULAR
LOOK WE THINK, AT THE
CONCLUSIONS MUELLER MADE ABOUT
OBSTRUCTION, WHY HE CHOSE TO
MAKE NO CONCLUSION
IN THE WORDS OF "THE POST" THERE
ARE WAYS IN WHICH YOU COULD READ
THE PRESIDENT'S ACTIONS AS
INNOCENT.
>> I THINK DEMOCRATS ARE ALL
POISED TO TAKE OVER THE
WEEKEND'S AIR, BETTING THIS IS
GOING TO BE DISPOSITIVE.
NOT CLEAR IT'S GOING TO BE
DISPOSITIVE.
>> ANY SIGN THAT THE MARKET
CARES AT THIS POINT?
>> NO.
>> COMPLETELY ACADEMIC
>> VINDICATION OF A PRESIDENT
WHO LOVE THE STOCK MARKET.
THE GUY DOES LOVE THE STOCK
MARKET
HE WANTS IT HIGHER
WE GET A MISSILE LAUNCH, NORTH
KOREA, NOBODY CARES.
WE GET -- BECAUSE WE IMMEDIATELY
GET -- PEOPLE GET PUT OUT ABOUT
HOW TALKS ARE CLOSE, TALKS ARE
CLOSE, TALKS ARE CLOSE
ANY TIME THE STOCK MARKET GOES
DOWN, THE TALKS ARE CLOSE.
>> AS FOR THE PRESSER ITSELF, A
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT SPOKESPERSON
DID SAY THIS MORNING THAT IT
WILL ADDRESS THE DEGREE TO WHICH
THE WHITE HOUSE INVOKED
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE ON ANY OF
THIS, THE INTERACTION THAT
JUSTICE HAS HAD WITH THE WHITE
HOUSE PRIOR TO THIS DISCLOSURE
TODAY AND THEN FINALLY THE
PROCESS THAT THEY'VE USED FOR
REDA
REDACTION, TO THE DEGREE IT'S
USED
AGAIN, THEY SAY IT'S NOT GOING
TO BE THAT HEAVY.
>> LOOK, IT WILL MAKE GOOD
READING, BUT IT'S A DIFFERENT
CHANNEL.
WE HAVE TO COVER IT CLEARLY,
BECAUSE YOU KNOW DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING TO BE IN IT
FOR US, IT'S VERY HARD TO SAY
WHAT THIS IS GOING TO DO, OTHER
THAN BE EXCITING AND
ENTERTAINING
WE'RE ALL GOING TO READ IT, I
THINK.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE A NETFLIX
STORY, RIGHT
$15.99.
>> NOT THAT MUCH, IS IT?
>> THAT'S THE NEW PRICE, PREMIUM
PRICE.
>> $15.99?
ALL THE STREAMS I WANT
WHAT KIND OF STREAMS DO I GET
WITH $15.99 NETFLIX?
>> UNLIMITED.
>> THANK YOU.
>> IF YOU REFERENCE FIREFEST.
>> YES.
>> BIG HIT, FIREFEST.
>> FIREFEST REALLY STAYED WITH
YOU.
>> DAVID, IT WAS A CONCERT THAT
DIDN'T OCCUR.
>> I'M AWARE.
>> BUT WHAT WAS IT, SOMEBODY
WANTED -- JUST KIDDING, I KNOW
BUT I THINK THIS IS LIKE THE
MOVIES
IT COULD HAVE GONE EITHER WAY.
>> MAYBE IMPLICATIONS ON THE
PRESIDENT'S RELATIONSHIP WITH
CHINA AND TRADE WHICH, BY THE
WAY, WE'RE NOW GETTING REPORTS
ABOUT MAYBE SOMETHING BY THE END
OF MAY
CHINA SAYS THERE'S STILL WORK TO
BE DONE.
DIM NOCHLT, BY THE WAY, ON THE
TAPE THIS MORNING, JAMIE DIMON.
>> ONE THING THAT WASN'T
MENTIONED WAS OXY.
REMEMBER FENTANYL, THE PRESIDENT
CARES PASSIONATELY ABOUT THE
DUMPING OF FENTANYL.
>> WE HAVE AN OPIOID CRISIS IN
THIS COUNTRY.
>> YES, WE DO.
>> IT'S MADE LARGELY IN CHINA.
>> BUT THEY SAID THEY WOULD
START.
>> YES, THEY SAID THEY WOULD
CRACK DOWN
IT'S NOT MONOLITHIC.
YOU KNOW, CHINA IS --
>> LOOK, THE CHINESE DO THIS
THEY EXECUTE FOR WHITE COLLAR.
>> IT'S A POSITIVE, CERTAINLY,
IN TERMS OF TRYING TO DEAL WITH
OUR ENORMOUS OPIOID CRISIS IN
THIS COUNTRY
SO MANY DEATHS.
>> THAT WAS AFTER NAVARRO'S
SPEECH WHERE HE SAID I'LL KNOW
YOUR INTENT IF YOU STOP THE
FENTANYL AND THEN THEY SAID
WE'RE GOING TO PUT REAL
SANCTIONS.
SANCTIONS THERE USUALLY MEANS
EXECUTION.
>> YEAH.
>> THERE'S BEN SILVERMAN ON THE
POST OF THE EXCHANGE NEXT TO
STACEY CUNNINGHAM OF THE NEW
YORK STOCK EXCHANGE.
HAVEN'T HEARD A LOT FROM BEN
HE HAS MADE SOME APPEARANCES AT
RECODE CONFERENCE OUT IN
CALIFORNIA
INVESTORS WILL GET TO KNOW HIM
IN A HURRY.
>> YEAH.
THIS IS THE BENIGN PLAY.
IT'S BENIGN.
IT DIDN'T HURT ANYBODY.
>> DIDN'T HURT ANYBODY
THEY'RE NOT ABOUT SHARING.
>> NO.
THEY'RE ABOUT YOU BUYING SHOES.
>> GOING DEEP ON YOU, EXPLORING
YOURSELF.
>> RIGHT, EXPLORE YOURSELF
WHILE WE'RE WAITING, UNION
PACIFIC IS UP $6, OKAY
THAT IS, AGAIN, CSX.
I DEFY YOU TO TELL ME THAT THE
ECONOMY IS NOT GETTING BETTER
AND BETTER.
>> WE'LL TALK TO LANCE FRITZ AT
10:30.
>> SO GOOD
ASK HIM ABOUT HIRING PEOPLE
COMING OUT OF JAIL
SO GOOD AT THAT.
>> THE DEGREE TO WHICH THEY'VE
TAKEN SHARE.
THEIR PRICING POWER BECOMES MORE
EVIDENT.
>> FABULOUS CEO, SO UMBLE.
I'VE TRIED TO GET HIM TO SAY
BASICALLY HOW GOOD THEY ARE.
THAT'S NOT HIS STYLE
BUT HE IS A REALLY GOOD CEO.
>> ZOOM, THE OTHER MAJOR IPO
TODAY.
BOTH OF THESE NAMES, BY THE WAY,
WELL OVER SUBSCRIBED
I THINK 20 TIMES THE CASE I'VE
HEARD FOR PINTEREST.
MORE THAN THAT FOR ZOOM.
WE'LL SEE HOW THEY PERFORM AFTER
MARKET
THE EXPECTATIONS ARE, GIVEN THE
DEMAND FOR ZOOM.
>> WE'LL TALK TO ERIC HUANG
LATER WHO SAYS HOW HIS VISA WAS
REJECTED TWO TIMES AND IT WAS
FINALLY APPROVED
HE IS SET TO BE A BILLIONAIRE
TODAY.
>> THEY'RE TOP OF THE GAME
GREAT PRODUCT.
IT'S SOMETHING TANGIBLE THAT
PEOPLE GET AHOLD OF GREAT
PRODUCT.
THE MOST EXPENSIVE STOCK THAT'S
PROFITABLE
MOST EXPENSIVE ONE
BIGGER THAN THAT LAST.
[ BELL RINGS ]
>> THERE'S THE OPENING BELL.
NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE AND THE
NASDAQ
PINTEREST, WE'LL TALK WITH CEO
BEN SILVERMAN AFTER THE OPENING
TRADE AT THE NASDAQ, IT IS ZOOM.
>> TODAY IS A DAY WE'RE TRYING
TO FIND OUT IF BERNIE SANDERS
WILL CONTINUE TO KILL THIS
MARKET
ONE THING THAT KILLED THE HEALTH
CARE STOCKS.
IT WAS, LET'S SAY, THE STRAW
THAT BROKE THE CAMEL'S BACK WHEN
BERNIE SANDERS CAME ON, MEDICARE
FOR ALL.
WAIT A SECOND, REPUBLICANS, OR
ELSE THEY WOULDN'T HAVE HIM ON,
DEMOCRATS, PRESIDENT
AND THEY STILL CAN'T RECOVER.
>> THERE'S A LOT OF DISCUSSION
ABOUT THIS
HEALTH CARE HAS UNDERPERFORMED
THE S&P OVER THE LAST TEN DAYS,
THE MOST IN TEN YEARS.
DO INVESTORS REALLY BELIEVE
DEMOCRATS WILL TAKE THE WHITE
HOUSE AND THE SENATE WHERE THEY
HAVE ABOUT A THIRD PERCENT --
30% CHANCE
>> IT'S A GREAT QUESTION
I THINK THEY FEAR WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN OBAMA GOT IN.
THEN THEY HAD BOTH THE HOUSE AND
SENATE, WHEN THESE WENT TO AN
EIGHT TIMES, EIGHT
PROFITS OVER NINE, TEN YEARS
I THINK THE SELLERS WILL COME
BACK, BUT IT'S GETTING NEARER
WHERE YOU HAD GIGANTIC VOLUME AT
THE BOTTOM YESTERDAY FOR SOME OF
THESE.
THE SELLERS ARE ALMOST DONE.
AT THE SAME TIME, YOU DON'T WANT
TO OWN HEALTH CARE
YOU WANT TO OWN INDUSTRIALS.
AND THE INDUSTRIALS ARE SUCKING
UP ALL THE MONEY
HONEYWELL.
>> HONEYWELL, 192 BEATS 183.
>> STEVE TOUSA, THAT WAS HIS
FAVORITE STOCK
HE HAD ABOVE NUMBERS
HE WAS RIGHT ONCE AGAIN.
KIND OF ANNOYING HOW RIGHT HE
HAS BEEN
HONEYWELL WAS ABSOLUTELY
TERRIFIC
DYNAMITE
SIMPLE BUILDING CLIMATE WAS UP
NINE
REALLY AMAZING, DAVID.
>> DID NOT TAKE THE BAIT FROM
THE ACTIVIST IN TERMS OF A FULL
SPLIT BUT WENT ABOUT SOME
SMALLER DIVESTITURES.
>> RIGHT.
>> IS GREG COMING ON
>> HAYES
I'M NOT AWARE OF PLANS ON HIS
PART TO JOIN US ANY TIME SOON.
WE ALWAYS WELCOME MR. HAYES.
>> YOU'LL GET HIM AND I'LL SIT
BACK AND ENJOY THE -- PEOPLE ARE
STILL REELING FROM THE
MOLLENKOPF VERSUS COOK THING
I SAY BURY THE HATCHET.
>> CLEARLY MR. MOLLENKOPF WAS
INTERESTED IN BURYING THE
HATCHET.
QUALCOMM IS DOWN TODAY.
>> IT'S A MOTH TO FLAME.
>> A LOT MORE FOCUS ON 5G AS YOU
HAVE BEEN TALKING ABOUT, JIM.
>> RIGHT.
>> GIVEN THAT, IT REFOCUSED
PEOPLE ON THE OPPORTUNITY, IN
TERMS OF THE 5G CHIP SETS, APPLE
AND THE LARGER ECOSYSTEM
YOU MENTIONED ERICCSON EARLIER
IN TERMS OF THAT SIDE.
>> RIGHT
SOME SELLERS ARE COMING INTO
TECH TODAY, INTERESTING.
>> THEY DO SAY THEY THINK WE'RE
PAST THE BOTTOM OF THE CYCLE.
>> THEY DID.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> AND THEN SAMSUNG, OF COURSE,
ALL OF SOUTH KOREA WAS WEAK
BECAUSE OF THESE REPORTS ABOUT
THE GALAXY FOLD.
>> AND APPLE STOCK HAS BEEN
GOING UP EVER SINCE.
SAMSUNG IS STILL VERY MUCH DOING
A WILL THE OF STUFF, 5G,
CORNERED THEIR OWN MARKET.
I'VE NEVER SEEN A SITUATION
WHERE EVERYONE WAS BUYING A
STOCK OFF THE PHONE AND NOW
THEY'RE SELLING.
>>> LET'S GET TO THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT AND LISTEN TO THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL, WILLIAM BARR.
>> GOOD MORNING, EVERYBODY
THANKS FOR BEING HERE THIS
MORNING.
AS YOU KNOW, MARCH 22nd, SPECIAL
COUNSEL ROBERT MUELLER CONCLUDED
HIS INVESTIGATION INTO MATTERS
RELATED TO RUSSIAN ATTEMPTS TO
INTERFERE IN OUR 2016
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION, AND HE
SUBMITTED HIS CONFIDENTIAL
REPORT TO ME, PURSUANT TO
DEPARTMENT REGULATIONS
AS I SAID DURING MY SENATE
CONFIRMATION HEARING AND SINCE,
I'M COMMITTED TO ENSURING THE
GREATEST DEGREE POSSIBLE OF
TRANSPARENCY CONCERNING THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL'S INVESTIGATION,
CONSISTENT WITH THE LAW.
AT 11:00 THIS MORNING, I'M GOING
TO TRANSMIT COPIES OF THE PUBLIC
VERSION OF THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S
REPORT TO THE CHAIRMAN AND
RANKING MEMBERS OF THE SENATE
AND HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEES
THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE WILL
ALSO MAKE THE REPORT AVAILABLE
TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE BY
POSTING IT ON THE DEPARTMENT'S
WEBSITE AFTER IT HAS BEEN
DELIVERED TO CONGRESS.
I WOULD LIKE TO MAKE A FEW
COMMENTS TODAY ON THE REPORT
BEFORE I DO THAT, I WANT TO
THANK DEPUTY ATTORNEY GENERAL
ROD ROSENSTEIN FOR JOINING ME
HERE TODAY AND FOR HIS
ASSISTANCE AND COUNSEL
THROUGHOUT THIS PROCESS.
ROD, AS YOU KNOW, HAS SERVED AT
THE DEPARTMENT FOR NEARLY 30
YEARS WITH DEDICATION AND
DISTINCTION AND IT'S BEEN A
GREAT PRIVILEGE AND PLEASURE FOR
ME TO WORK WITH HIM SINCE MY
CONFIRMATION
HE HAD WELL-DESERVED PLANS TO
STEP BACK FROM PUBLIC SERVICE
THAT WERE INTERRUPTED BY MY
ASKING HIM TO HELP IN MY
TRANSITION
ROD HAS BEEN AN INVALUABLE
PARTNER, AND I AM GRATEFUL THAT
HE IS WILLING TO HELP ME AND HAS
BEEN ABLE TO SEE THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S INVESTIGATION THROUGH
TO ITS CONCLUSION.
THANKS, ROD.
I WOULD ALSO LIKE TO THANK
SPECIAL COUNSEL ROBERT MUELLER
FOR HIS SERVICE AND THE
THOROUGHNESS OF HIS
INVESTIGATION, PARTICULARLY HIS
WORK EXPOSING THE NATURE OF
RUSSIA'S ATTEMPTS TO INTERFERE
WITH OUR ELECTORAL PROCESS
AS YOU KNOW, ONE OF THE PRIMARY
PURPOSES OF THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S INVESTIGATION WAS TO
DETERMINE WHETHER PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S CAMPAIGN OR ANY
INDIVIDUAL ASSOCIATED WITH IT
CONSPIRED OR COORDINATED WITH
THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT TO
INTERFERE IN THE 2016 ELECTION
VOLUME ONE OF THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S REPORT DESCRIBES THE
RESULTS OF THAT INVESTIGATION.
AS YOU WILL SEE THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S REPORT STATES THAT
HIS, QUOTE, INVESTIGATION DID
NOT ESTABLISH THAT MEMBERS OF
THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN CONSPIRED OR
COORDINATED WITH THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT IN ITS ELECTION
INTERFERENCE ACTIVITIES.
I AM SURE THAT ALL AMERICANS
SHARE MY CONCERN ABOUT THE
EFFORTS OF THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT TO INTERFERE IN OUR
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION.
AS THE SPECIAL COUNSEL REPORT
MAKES CLEAR, THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT SOUGHT TO INTERFERE
IN OUR ELECTION PROCESS, BUT
THANKS TO THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S
THOROUGH INVESTIGATION, WE NOW
KNOW THAT THE RUSSIAN OPERATIVES
WHO PERPETRATED THESE SCHEMES
DID NOT HAVE THE COOPERATION OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP OR THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN, OR THE KNOWING
ASSISTANCE OF ANY OTHER AMERICAN
FOR THAT MATTER.
THAT IS SOMETHING THAT ALL
AMERICANS CAN AND SHOULD BE
GRATEFUL TO HAVE CONFIRMED
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL REPORT
OUTLINES TWO MAIN EFFORTS BY THE
RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT TO INFLUENCE
THE 2016 ELECTION.
FIRST, THE REPORT DETAILS
EFFORTS BY THE INTERNET RESEARCH
AGENCY, A RUSSIAN COMPANY WITH
CLOSE TIES TO THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT, TO SOW SOCIAL
DISCORD IN AMERICAN VOTERS BY
SPREADING MISINFORMATION
CHARGES IN FEDERAL COURT WERE
BROUGHT AGAINST SEVERAL RUSSIAN
INTERNATIONALS AND ENTITIES FOR
THEIR RESPECTIVE ROLES IN THIS
SCHEME
THOSE CHARGES REMAIN PENDING AND
THE INDIVIDUAL DEFENDANTS REMAIN
AT LARGE
BUT THE SPECIAL COUNSEL FOUND NO
EVIDENCE THAT ANY AMERICAN,
INCLUDING ANYONE ASSOCIATED WITH
THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN, CONSPIRED OR
COORDINATED WITH THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT OR THE IRA IN THIS
ILLEGAL SCHEME
INDEED, AS THE REPORT STATES,
QUOTE, THE INVESTIGATION DID NOT
IDENTIFY EVIDENCE THAT ANY U.S.
PERSON, KNOWINGLY OR
INTENTIONALLY, COORDINATED WITH
THE IRA'S INTERFERENCE
OPERATION, UNQUOTE
PUT ANOTHER WAY, THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL FOUND NO COLLUSION BY
ANY AMERICANS IN IRA'S ILLEGAL
ACTIVITIES
SECOND, THE REPORT DETAILS
EFFORTS BY THE RUSSIAN MILITARY
INTELLIGENCE ORGANIZATION TO
HACK INTO COMPUTERS AND STEAL
DOCUMENTS AND EMAILS FROM
INDIVIDUALS ASSOCIATED WITH
DEMOCRATIC PARTY AND HILLARY
CLINTON'S CAMPAIGN FOR THE
PURPOSE OF EVENTUALLY
PUBLICIZING THESE DOCUMENTS.
OBTAINING SUCH UNAUTHORIZE D
FOLLOWING A THOROUGH
INVESTIGATION OF THESE HACKING
OPERATIONS, THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
BROUGHT CHARGES AGAINST RUSSIAN
MILITARY OFFICERS FOR THEIR
RESPECTIVE ROLES IN THESE
ILLEGAL HACKING OPERATIONS
THOSE CHARGES ARE STILL PENDING
AND THE DEFENDANTS REMAIN AT
LARGE.
BUT AGAIN, THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S
REPORT DID NOT FIND ANY EVIDENCE
THAT MEMBERS OF THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN OR ANYONE ASSOCIATED
WITH THE CAMPAIGN CONSPIRE D OR
COORDINATED WITH THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT IN THESE HACKING
OPERATIONS
IN OTHER WORDS, THERE WAS NO
EVIDENCE OF THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN
COLLUSION WITH THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT'S HACKING
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S
INVESTIGATION ALSO EXAMINED
RUSSIAN EFFORTS TO PUBLISH
STOLEN EMAILS AND DOCUMENTS ON
THE INTERNET
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL FOUND THAT
AFTER THE GIU DISSEMINATED SOME
OF THE STOLEN DOCUMENTS TO
ENTITIES THAT IT CONTROLLED,
D.C. LEAKS AND GOOSIFER TWO, GIU
TRANSFERRED SOME OF THE
DOCUMENTS TO WIKILEAKS FOR
PUBLICATION.
WIKILEAKS THEN MADE A SERIES OF
DOCUMENT DUMPS
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL ALSO
INVESTIGATED WHETHER ANY MEMBER
OR AFFILIATE OF THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN ENCOURAGED OR OTHERWISE
PLAYED A ROLE IN THESE DIS
DISEMANATION EFFORTS
THESE ACTS WOULD NOT BE CRIMINAL
UNLESS THE PUBLISHER ALSO
PARTICIPATED IN THE UNDERLYING
HACKING CONSPIRACY
HERETO, THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S
REPORT DID NOT FIND THAT ANY
PERSON ASSOCIATED WITH THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN ILLEGALLY PARTICIPATED
IN THE DISEMINATION OF THE
MATERIALS.
DURING THE 2016 PRESIDENTIAL
CAMPAIGN, AFTER REVIEWING THESE
CONTACTS, THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
DID NOT FIND ANY CONSPIRACY TO
VIOLATE U.S. LAW INVOLVING
RUSSIAN LINKED PERSONS AND ANY
PERSONS LINKED WITH THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN
THAT'S THE BOTTOM LINE
AFTER NEARLY TWO YEARS OF
INVESTIGATION, THOUSANDS OF
SUBPOENAS, HUNDREDS OF WARRANTS
AND WITNESS INTERVIEWS, THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL CONFIRM ED TO
INTERFERE WITH THE 2016
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION BUT DID
NOT FIND THAT THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN
OR OTHER AMERICANS CLOOUDED IN
THOSE EFFORTS.
AFTER FINDING NO UNDERLYING
COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA, THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL'S REPORT GOES ON
TO CONSIDER WHETHER CERTAIN
ACTIONS OF THE PRESIDENT COULD
AMOUNT TO OBSTRUCTION OF THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL'S INVESTIGATION.
AS I ADDRESSED IN MY MARCH 24th
LETTER, THE SPECIAL COUNSEL DID
NOT MAKE A PROSECUTORIAL
DECISION REGARDING THIS
ALLEGATION
TEN EPISODES INVOLVING THE
PRESIDENT AND DISCUSSES
POTENTIAL LEGAL THEORIES OF
CONNECTING THOSE TO AN
OBSTRUCTION OFFENSE.
AFTER REVIEWING THE THEORIES
OUTLINED IN THE REPORT AND WITH
CONSULTATION OF THE OFFICE OF
LEGAL COUNSEL AND OTHER LAWYERS,
THE DEPUTY ATTORNEY GENERAL AND
I CONCLUDED THAT THE EVIDENCE
DEVELOPED BY THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
IS NOT SUFFICIENT TO ESTABLISH
THAT THE PRESIDENT COMMITTED AN
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE OFFENSE
ALTHOUGH THE DEPUTY ATTORNEY
GENERAL AND I DISAGREED WITH
SOME OF THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S
LEGAL THEORIES AND FELT THAT
SOME OF THE EPISODES EXAMINED
DID NOT AMOUNT TO OBSTRUCTION AS
A MATTER OF LAW, WE DID NOT RELY
SOLELY ON THAT IN MAKING OUR
DECISION
INSTEAD, WE ACCEPTED THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S LEGAL FRAMEWORK FOR
PURPOSES OF OUR ANALYSIS AND
EVALUATED THE EVIDENCE AS
PRESENTED BY THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
IN REACHING OUR CONCLUSIONS.
IN ASSESSING THE PRESIDENT'S
ACTIONS DISCUSSED IN THE REPORT,
IT IS IMPORTANT TO BEAR IN MIND
THE CONTEXT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP FACED AN
UNPRECEDENTED SITUATION.
AS HE ENTERED INTO OFFICE AND
SOUGHT TO PERFORM HIS
RESPONSIBILITIES AS PRESIDENT,
FEDERAL AGENTS AND PROSECUTORS
WERE SCRUTINIZING HIS CONDUCT
BEFORE AND AFTER TAKING OFFICE
AND THE CONDUCT OF SOME OF HIS
ASSOCIATES
AT THE SAME TIME, THERE WAS
RELENTLESS SPECULATION IN THE
NEWS MEDIA ABOUT THE PRESIDENT'S
PERSONAL CULPABILITY, YET AS HE
SAID FROM THE BEGINNING, THERE
WAS, IN FACT, NO COLLUSION
AND AS THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S
REPORT ACKNOWLEDGES, THERE IS
SUBSTANTIAL EVIDENCE TO SHOW
THAT THE PRESIDENT WAS
FRUSTRATED AND ANGERED BY HIS
SINCERE BELIEF THAT THE
INVESTIGATION WAS UNDERMINING
HIS PRESIDENCY, PROPELLED BY HIS
POLITICAL OPPONENTS AND FUELED
BY ILLEGAL LEAKS
NONETHELESS, THE WHITE HOUSE
FULLY COOPERATED WITH THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL'S INVESTIGATION,
PROVIDING UNFEDDERED ACCESS TO
CAMPAIGN AND WHITE HOUSE
DOCUMENTS, DIRECTING SENIOR
AIDES TO TESTIFY FREELY AND
ASSERTING NO PRIVILEGE CLAIMS.
AT THE SAME TIME THE PRESIDENT
TOOK NO ACT THAT, IN FACT,
DEPRIVED THE SPECIAL COUNSEL OF
THE DOCUMENTS AND WITNESSES
NECESSARY TO COMPLETE HIS
INVESTIGATION.
APARTMENT FROM WHETHER THE ACTS
WERE OBSTRUCTIVE, THIS EVIDENCE
OF NONCORRUPT MOTIVES WEIGHS
HEAVILY AGAINST ANY ALLEGATION
THAT THE PRESIDENT HAD A CORRUPT
INTENT TO OBSTRUCT THE
INVESTIGATION.
NOW BEFORE I TAKE QUESTIONS, I
WANT TO ADDRESS A FEW ASPECTS OF
THE PROCESS FOR PRODUCING THE
PUBLIC REPORT THAT I AM
RELEASING TODAY.
AS I SAID SEVERAL TIMES, THE
REPORT CONTAINS LIMITED
REDACTIONS, RELATED TO FOUR
CATEGORIES OF INFORMATION.
TO ENSURE AS MUCH TRANSPARENCY
AS POSSIBLE, THOSE REDACTIONS
HAVE BEEN CLEARLY LABELED SO
THAT THE READERS CAN TELL WHICH
REDACTIONS CORRESPOND TO WHICH
CATEGORIES
AS I DO RECALL, THOSE CATEGORIES
ARE 6E MATERIAL, GRAND JURY
MATERIAL, INFORMATION THAT THE
IC BELIEVES WOULD DISCLOSE
SOURCES AND METHODS, INFORMATION
THAT WOULD IMPAIR THE
INVESTIGATION AND PROSECUTION OF
OTHER CASES THAT ARE UNDER WAY
AND, FINALLY, INFORMATION THAT
IMPLICATES THE PRIVACY AND
REPUTATIONAL INTERESTS OF
PERIPHERAL THIRD PARTIES
AS YOU WILL SEE, MOST OF THE
REDACTIONS WERE COMPELLED BY THE
NEED TO PREVENT HARM TO ONGOING
MATTERS AND TO COMPLY WITH COURT
ORDERS, PROHIBITING THE PUBLIC
DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION
BEARING ON ONGOING
INVESTIGATIONS IN CRIMINAL
CASES, SUCH AS THE IRA CASE AND
THE ROGER STONE CASE
THESE REDACTIONS WERE APPLIED BY
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE ATTORNEYS,
WORKING CLOSELY TOGETHER WITH
ATTORNEYS FROM THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S OFFICE AS WELL AS THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY AND
PROSECUTORS THAT ARE HANDLING
THE ONGOING CASES.
THE REDACTIONS ARE THEIR WORK
PRODUCT.
NO REDACTIONS DONE BY ANYBODY
OUTSIDE THIS GROUP
THERE WERE NO REDACTIONS DONE BY
ANYBODY OUTSIDE THIS GROUP
NO ONE OUTSIDE THIS GROUP
PROPOSED ANY REDACTIONS AND NO
ONE OUTSIDE THE DEPARTMENT HAS
SEEN THE UNREDACTED REPORT WITH
THE EXCEPTION OF CERTAIN
SECTIONS THAT WERE MADE
AVAILABLE TO I.C., THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY FOR THEIR
ADVICE OR PROTECTING
INTELLIGENCE SOURCES
CONSISTENT WITH LONGSTANDING
EXECUTIVE BRANCH PRACTICE, THE
DECISION WHETHER TO ASSERT
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE OVER ANY
PORTION OF THE REPORT RESTED
WITH THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES
BECAUSE THE WHITE HOUSE HAD
VOLUNTARILY COOPERATED WITH THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL, SIGNIFICANT
PORTIONS OF THE REPORT CONTAINED
MATERIAL OVER WHICH THE
PRESIDENT COULD HAVE ASSERTED
PRIVILEGE.
AND HE WOULD HAVE BEEN WELL
WITHIN HIS RIGHTS TO DO SO
FOLLOWING MY MARCH 29th LETTER,
THE OFFICE OF THE WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL REQUESTED THE
OPPORTUNITY TO REVIEW THE
REDACTED VERSION OF THE REPORT
IN ORDER TO ADVISE THE PRESIDENT
AND THE POTENTIAL INVOCATION OF
PRIVILEGE, WHICH IS CONSISTENT
WITH LONGSTANDING PRACTICE
FOLLOWING THAT REVIEW, THE
PRESIDENT CONFIRMED THAT IN THE
INTEREST OF TRANSPARENCY AND
FULL DISCLOSURE TO THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE, HE WOULD NOT ASSERT
PRIVILEGE OVER THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S REPORT
ACCORDINGLY, THE PUBLIC REPORT I
AM RELEASING TODAY CONTAINS
REDACTIONS ONLY FOR THE FOUR
CATEGORIES THAT I PREVIOUSLY
OUTLINED AND NO MATERIAL HAS
BEEN REDACTED BASED ON EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE.
IN ADDITION, EARLIER THIS WEEK,
THE PRESIDENT'S PERSONAL COUNSEL
REQUESTED AND WAS GIVEN THE
OPPORTUNITY TO READ A FINAL
VERSION OF THE REDACTED REPORT
BEFORE IT WAS PUBLICLY RELEASED.
THAT REQUEST WAS CONSISTENT WITH
THE PRACTICE FOLLOWED UNDER THE
ETHICS AND GOVERNMENT ACT, WHICH
PERMITTED INDIVIDUALS NAMED IN A
REPORT PREPARED BY INDEPENDENT
COUNSEL THE OPPORTUNITY TO READ
THE REPORT BEFORE PUBLICATION.
THE PRESIDENT'S PERSONAL LAWYERS
WERE NOT PERMITTED TO MAKE AND
DID NOT REQUEST ANY REDACTIONS
IN ADDITION TO MAKING THE
REDACTED REPORT PUBLIC, WE ARE
ALSO WORKING WITH CONGRESS TO
ACCOMMODATE THEIR LEGITIMATE
OVERSIGHT INTEREST WITH RESPECT
TO THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S
INVESTIGATION.
WE HAVE BEEN CONSULTING WITH
CHAIRMAN GRAHAM AND CHAIRMAN
NADLER THROUGH THIS PROCESS AND
WE WILL CONTINUE TO DO  THE LIM
REDACTIONS, I BELIEVE THAT THE
PUBLICLY RELEASED REPORT WILL
ALLOW EVERY AMERICAN TO
UNDERSTAND THE RESULTS OF THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL'S INVESTIGATION.
NEVERTHELESS, IN AN EFFORT TO
ACCOMMODATE CONGRESSIONAL
REQUESTS, WE WILL MAKE
AVAILABLE, SUBJECT TO
APPROPRIATE SAFEGUARDS, TO A
BIPARTISAN GROUP OF LEADERS FROM
SEVERAL CONGRESSIONAL COMMITTEES
A VERSION OF THE REPORT WITH ALL
REDACTIONS REMOVED EXCEPT THOSE
RELATING TO GRAND JURY
INFORMATION.
THUS THESE MEMBERS OF CONGRESS
WILL BE ABLE TO SEE ALL OF THE
REDACTED MATERIAL FOR THEMSELVES
WITH A LIMITED EXCEPTION OF THAT
WHICH BY LAW CANNOT BE SHARED.
I BELIEVE THAT THIS
ACCOMMODATION, TOGETHER WITH MY
UPCOMING TESTIMONY BEFORE THE
SENATE AND HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEES, WILL SATISFY ANY
NEED CONGRESS HAS FOR
INFORMATION REGARDING THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL'S INVESTIGATION.
ONCE AGAIN, I WOULD LIKE TO
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE, AND I
WILL NOW HAVE A FEW QUESTIONS.
>> MR. ATTORNEY GENERAL, WE
DON'T HAVE THE REPORT IN HAND.
SO COULD YOU EXPLAIN FOR US THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL'S ARTICULATED
REASON FOR NOT REACHING A
DECISION ON OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE AND IF IT HAD ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THE DEPARTMENT'S
LONG-STANDING GUIDANCE ON NOT
INDICTING A SITTING PRESIDENT
AND YOU SAY YOU DISAGREE WITH
SOME OF HIS LEGAL THEORIES, WHAT
DID YOU DISAGREE WITH HIM ON
>> THE -- I LEAVE IT TO HIS
DESCRIPTION IN THE REPORT, THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL'S OWN
ARTICULATION OF WHY HE DID NOT
WANT TO MAKE A DETERMINATION AS
TO WHETHER OR NOT THERE WAS AN
OBSTRUCTION OFFENSE.
PUT I WILL SAY WHEN WE MET WITH
HIM, DEPUTY ATTORNEY GENERAL
ROSENSTEIN AND I MET WITH HIM
ALONG WITH ED OWE CALLAHAN, WHO
IS THE PRINCIPLE ASSOCIATE
DE
DEPUTY, ON MARCH 5th, WE
SPECIFICALLY ASKED HIM ABOUT THE
OLC OPINION AND WHETHER OR
NOT --
>> A SPLIT SCREEN THERE BETWEEN
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL AND THE
INDICATION ON PINTEREST, 21 TO
22 THE HEADLINES OUT OF THE
JUSTICE PRESSER, THE REPORT OUT
OF THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S OFFICE
CONFIRMS THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT
DID SEEK TO MEDDLE IN THE 2016
CAMPAIGN, DID NOT HAVE THE
COOPERATION OF THE PRESIDENT OR
HIS CAMPAIGN, REFERENCE TO TEN
EPISODES INVOLVING POTENTIAL
OBSTRUCTION BY THE PRESIDENT,
BUT THE ATTORNEY GENERAL GOING
ON TO SAY THAT THE EVIDENCE OF
NONCORRUPT MOTIVES WEIGH HEAVILY
AGAINST THOSE ALLEGATIONS.
EAMON JAVERS, WE HAVE THE PRESS
CONFERENCE NOW UNDER OUR BELTS
AND WE WILL AWAIT THE HARD COPY.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
I THINK THE MOST SIGNIFICANT
THING YOU HEARD THERE FROM THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL IS ON THAT
ISSUE THAT YOU MENTIONED OF
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE, WHAT
HE'S SAYING THERE GOES A LITTLE
BIT FURTHER IN TERMS OF
EXPLANATION FOR HIS OWN DECISION
AS TO WHY MUELLER'S FINDINGS ON
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE
ULTIMATELY DON'T MOUNT TO A
CHARGEABLE OFFENSE HERE OF
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE
WHAT BARR IS SAYING IS THOUGH
THERE MAY BE EVIDENCE OF
OBSTRUCTIVE ACTS BY THE
PRESIDENT THAT WE'LL READ ABOUT
IN THIS REPORT, ULTIMATELY THE
PRESIDENT DIDN'T HAVE CORRUPT
INTENT BECAUSE HE ALSO DIDN'T
FIRE MUELLER, DIDN'T TAKE ANY
STEPS TO BLOCK THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S INVESTIGATION, AND HE
SAYS THAT GOES A LONG WAY TO
GETTING PAST THIS IDEA THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAD ANY CRIMINAL
INTENT IN TERMS OF OBSTRUCTION
OF JUSTICE
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL THERE
SUGGESTING THAT MAYBE IF THE
PRESIDENT HAD TAKEN SOME OF
THOSE STEPS, IT MIGHT BE A
DIFFERENT SITUATION.
BUT BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT
COOPERATED FULLY, DIDN'T TAKE
ANY STEPS TO BLOCK THE
INVESTIGATION, AND THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL'S MIND, THIS WASN'T
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
>> ALL RIGHT
UNFETTERED ACCESS TO DOCUMENTS,
ASSERTING NO PRIVILEGE, NO
PROPOSED REDACTIONS, WE'LL KEEP
OUR EYE ON THIS STORY LATER ON
THIS MORNING
IN THE MEANTIME, JIM, DOW ADDED
TO ITS GAINS SLIGHTLY ON THE
NEWS
>> YEAH.
LOOK, I THINK ANYTHING THAT
MAKES THE PRESIDENT IS CLEARLY
VIEWED AS BEING PRO STOCK.
THIS PINTEREST, WANT TO GO OVER
THIS AGAIN, IT IS EXPENSIVE.
BUT NO ONE THINKS -- IT IS NOT
IT IS GOING TO BE PROPABLE NEXT
YEAR
BUT IT IS THE CHIP
PEOPLE WANT SOMETHING INTERNET
THAT IS FRESH FACED AND VIEWED
AS BEING A POSITIVE COMPANY.
ACTUAL POSITIVE COMPANY.
AND PINTEREST IS THAT.
I THINK IT WILL BRING IN SELLING
OF OTHER TECHES THAT -- BECAUSE
COMPANIES THAT ARE BUYING
PINTEREST DON'T HAVE ENOUGH
MONEY TO TAKE IN PINTEREST AND
NOT HAVE TO SELL SOMETHING
I SAY PRESSURE ON FACEBOOK HERE.
>> SEE ANY INDICATION MOVE UP
22, 23 NOW, PRICING AT $19
THAT WOULD GIVE IT A MARKET CAP
ABOVE $12 BILLION.
ACTUALLY A BIT MORE.
ABOVE THE LAST ROUND --
>> THAT'S IMPORTANT.
I THINK WE'RE ITCHING FOR
SOMETHING THAT WE CAN HAVE THAT
IS NEW, THAT ISN'T TWITTER, THAT
ISN'T FACEBOOK
THIS IS THE KINDLER, GENTLER
INTERNET PLAY.
BUT I DON'T KNOW IF THERE IS
ENOUGH MONEY AROUND TO OWN
FACEBOOK AND PINTEREST IF YOU
ARE A BIG TECH BUYER
JUST DON'T KNOW IF THERE IS.
BY THE WAY, LET'S LUMP IN A
SALES FORCE.
SMALL ACQUISITION, I THOUGHT IT
WAS GOOD
SELL SALES FORCE TO BUY
PINTEREST.
ONCE YOU START GETTING REAL GOOD
COMPANIES -- PINTEREST IS NOT A
BAD COMPANY.
IF YOU CAN STOMACH IT, YOU CAN
BUY FACEBOOK
ON THE DAY LIKE TODAY, PEOPLE
REALIZE, I GOT TO SELL MORE,
PINTEREST IS OPENING UP HIGHER
THAN I THOUGHT
PEOPLE THOUGHT IT WOULD BE $16
TO $17.
>> THE INITIAL PROJECTED RANGE,
$15 TO $17
WE SHOULD WARN INVESTORS, IT IS
A DUAL CLASS STRUCTURE
YOU'RE GOING TO BUY CLASS A,
CLASS B HAS 20 VOTES A SHARE
>> I KNOW.
>> IT DOES SUNSET WITH THE
EXECUTIVES LEADING THE COMPANY,
WHICH IS DIFFERENT THAN LYFT,
WHICH DIDN'T HAVE THAT
PROVISION.
IT IS A GOOD POINT, CARL
THESE GOVERNANCE PROVISIONS ARE
IMPORTANT OR AT LEAST THEY DON'T
SEEM TO AFFECT THE WAY --
>> THEY DON'T.
AND LET'S SEE, IN TERMS OF WHAT
ELSE IS BEING SOLD, HEALTH CARE.
THEY CAN'T RALLY
EVERYBODY IS SO AFRAID WE'RE
GOING TO GET MEDICARE FOR ALL.
>> AND PRESCRIPTION DRUG PRICES.
>> THAT AND THE THOUGHT IF YOU
WERE TRULY WORRIED ABOUT A TRADE
WAR OR MUELLER, YOU WERE HIDING
IN SOME OF THESE DEFENSIVE NAMES
AND NOW THERE IS NO REASON TO --
>> LET'S SELL -- 8C.
>> UNITED HEALTH IS HOLDING ITS
OWN.
>> UP THREE AT ONE POINT
I'M USING MERCK AS THE TELL.
THEY'RE DOING VERY WELL.
MERCK IS JUST -- FROM 83 TO 72,
AND MERCK IS JUST KILLING
BRISTOL.
AND OPDIVO, BRISTOL, THESE ARE
MAJOR SHIFTS OUT OF MERCK INTO
THE UNITED TECHNOLOGIES.
>> YOU TWEETED A MOMENT AGO, THE
GAINER, TOP THREE GAINERS ON THE
S&P ARE MACRO NAMES.
UNITED RENTALS, SNAP-ON, UNP.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE SHORT
SNAP-ON, THOUGHT THEY WOULD
MISS
LILLY GOES DOWN AGAIN.
URI, FANTASTIC NUMBERS
UNION PACIFIC, I'M GLAD YOU
HAVE -- YOU CAN ASK HIM, ISN'T
THE COUNTRY DOING MUCH BETTER
AND HE MAY SAY, LOOK, SOME OF
THIS WAS BECAUSE WE HAD THE
WEST/EAST CHINA TRYING TO FILL
UP THE PIPE.
MOST OF IT IS BECAUSE WE HAVE
STRONG CATEGORIES ACROSS THE
BOARD.
>> AND, AGAIN, THE RESILIENCE OF
OUR ECONOMY VERSUS THE EUROPEAN
PMIs
APRIL, 47.8.
PRIOR WAS 47.5
VERY LITTLE --
>> SPAIN IS GOING TO COME OUT
AHEAD IN THIS PERIOD
AND A LOT OF THAT IS BECAUSE
THEY HAVE A STABLE POLITICAL
SYSTEM AND GREAT BANKING SYSTEM.
>> AND SPAIN
>> VERSUS GERMANY, THE BANKING
SYSTEM, EVERY DAY YOU HEAR
COMMERCE, DEUTSCHE THIS,
DEUTSCHE THAT.
>> I WAS WITH AN EXECUTIVE AT A
COMPANY THAT DOES A GREAT DEAL
OF BUSINESS IN EUROPE, AND IT IS
THE SAME REFRAIN, THINGS ARE
SLOW
>> SLOW.
>> PEPSICO HAD A GOOD QUARTER.
THERE YOU GO
PEPSICO.
JUDY HAWN, CREDIT SUISSE, THEY
BET AGAINST --
>> YOU CAN'T CAN EXPECT REAL
GROWTH OUT OF EUROPE, EVEN
GERMANY, TALKING NEGATIVE RATES.
>> OTHER THAN LAMBORGHINI,
BUILDING FIVE A DAY.
>> THEIR CAR REGISTRATIONS ARE
DOWN SEVEN MONTHS IN A ROW.
>> YOU CAN'T GET ONE
YOU CAN THANK HEAVENS YOU CAN'T.
MY WIFE WAS INTERESTED AFTER
GOING 180 MILES ON A SIDE
STREET
WE OUGHT TO GET ONE OF THESE
I SAID IT IS NOT LIKE THAT
WE HAVE A LOT OF HOUSES.
IT IS NOT LIKE, DON'T BE DAVID
FABER ON ME.
DON'T BUY A $40,000 CAR.
I LIVED IN MY CAR.
I'M NOT GOING TO PAY THE PRICE
OF A HOUSE.
>> WITH YOUR CORDUROY SUIT AND
YOUR --
>> CORDUROY SUIT.
>> WHAT DO YOU GOT TONIGHT
YOU GOT YOUR PICK OF TOPICS?
>> 5 BELOW IS A COMPANY THAT
MAKES -- YOU KNOW IT MAKES COLD
APPAREL, RIGHT
>> RIGHT
>> NO, IT IS FIVE TRINKETS
GO TO 5.50 BECAUSE OF THE
TARIFFS.
REI IS THE PLACE TO GO FOR COLD
EQUIPMENT.
>> I'M AWARE OF REI.
>> EIGHTH IN MARKET, WHERE MY
MOM SOLD LINGERIE WHEN SHE WAS A
YOUNG LADY.
>> THEY KNEW TEXTILES.
>> MY DAD SOLD GABERDINE
TROUSERS
SLACKS
>> SLACKS.
MY FATHER SAID, NO LONGER
TROUSERS, THEIR CALLED SLACKS.
I SAID, DAD, THEY'RE CALLED
PANTS.
>> JCPENNEY.
>> NUMBERS ARE BAD FOR SEPHORA
THAT'S WHY ULTA IS DOING SO
WELL.
>> WE'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT
"MAD MONEY" 6:00 P.M. EASTERN
TIME.
>> GREAT SHOW.
>> JUST TO RECAP SOME OF THE
DATA WE HAD IN THE PAST HOUR AND
A HALF
RETAIL SALES CAME IN AT 16 ABOVE
THE 1.0 ESTIMATE
CLAIMS 192
ONCE AGAIN A NEW 49-YEAR LOW
AND I THINK NOW LEADING ECONOMIC
INDICATORS
FOR THAT WE TURN TO RICK
SANTELLI
GOOD MORNING ONCE AGAIN.
>> GOOD MORNING.
LET'S GO IN CHRONOLOGICAL ORDER.
FEBRUARY READ ON BUSINESS
INVENTORIES.
EXPECTING A NUMBER UP THREE,
EXACTLY AS EXPECTED, UP .3%.
AND DO UNDERSTAND LAST MONTH
UP  .8%, THAT MAKES THE MONTH
OVER MONTH INVENTORIES THE
BIGGEST BACK TO MAY OF 2011 LAST
MONTH, UP .9%.
JUST TO THROW THAT OUT THERE
LEADING ECONOMIC INDICATORS IS A
MARCH READ
IT IS COMING IN ALSO LIKE SPOT
ON WITH EXPECTATIONS
UP .4%
WE DID LOSE .1% FROM .2% TO .1%
LAST MONTH
THEY'RE ALL SOLID NUMBERS.
A LITTLE WEAKNESS IN EUROPE.
THEY WEREN'T SO BAD.
BUND YIELDS TAPERED OFF.
OUR YIELDS ARE TAPERING OFF.
A LOT OF THAT HAS TO DO WITH THE
LONG WEEKEND AND, OF COURSE, A
BIG RUN OVER THE LAST TEN DAYS
IN THE INTEREST RATE COMPLEX
CARL AND THE GANG, BACK TO YOU
>> RICK, THANK YOU VERY MUCH
ONCE AGAIN, GOOD THURSDAY
MORNING, WELCOME BAH TO "SQUAWK
ON THE STREET.
I'M CARL QUINTANILLA WITH MORGAN
BRENNAN, DAVID FABER AT POST
NINE
SARA EISEN IS OFF TODAY.
MARKETS, INTERESTING ACTION IN
FIRST HALF HOUR.
WE WERE UP 100 ON THE DOW.
NOW UP 57.
S&P HAS GONE RED DESPITE SOME OF
THE GOOD DATA WE HAD SO FAR THIS
MORNING.
RICK, OF COURSE, JUST BRINGING
YOU REI, RETAIL SALES, CLAIMS,
AND PHILLY FED 85 WAS JUST A
TOUCH BELOW THE ESTIMATE OF 11
IN GENERAL, GUYS, IT HAS BEEN
SOLID MACRO COMMENTARY AND, OF
COURSE, HUGE ACTIVITY IN THE IPO
SPACE.
TWO TECH UNICORNS RACING TO THE
PUBLIC MARKETS THIS MORNING.
ONLINE IMAGE BOARD PINTEREST
READY TO BEGIN TRADING HERE IN A
MOMENT
$2 ABOVE THE HIGH END OF THE
RANGE AT $19
LATEST INDICATION $22, $23
ZOOM COMMUNICATIONS, PRICED AT
$36, VALUES THE COMPANY AT MORE
THAN $10 BILLION
FULL TEAM COVERAGE
BOB PISANI LOOKING AT PINTEREST
EARLY INDICATIONS HERE AT THE
EXCHANGE
JON FORTT AT THE NASDAQ COVERING
ZOOM
WE BEGIN WITH BOB AND PINTEREST
AT POST 8.
WHERE ARE YOU?
>> POST 8 COVERING THIS NUMBER,
ONLY CNBC INSIDE THE BOOTH
HERE IS WHERE THE ACTION
HAPPENS.
REMEMBER HOW THIS PROCESS WORKS.
THIS IS CALLED BUILDING THE
BOOK
YOU HAVE GOLDMAN SACHS
REPRESENTED THIS IS SHAWN HERE,
HE'S COMMUNICATING WITH GOLDMAN
SACHS, THEY'RE THE LEAD BOOK
RUNNER HERE, THERE ARE SEVERAL
BOOK RUNNERS THAT ARE PROVIDING
SHARES TO THE PUBLIC
BUT ALSO THE KEY IS GTS, WHO IS
THE MARKETMAKER HERE, AND
THEY'RE RIGHT THERE AS G
GLGLEN
GLEN CORAL, THE TWO OF THEM
TOGETHER WITH GOLDMAN AND THE
OTHER BOOK RUNNERS ARE BUILDING
THAT PARTICULAR BOOK
GETTING ORDERS TO BUY AND SELL
AT THE OPEN.
WHEN IS IT GOING TO HAPPEN
WE DON'T KNOW.
LET'S SEE IF WE CAN GET IN HERE
AND TALK TO PATTY MURPHY,
ANOTHER ONE OF THE DMs DOWN
HERE
WHAT IS THE INDICATION, ANY
INDICATION OF $22 TO $23
>> WHAT A GREAT COMPANY, FIRST
UNICORN, TECH UNICORN TO LIST ON
THE NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE IN
GTS IS VERY HONORED TO REPRESENT
THIS TRADE
WE HAVE A LOT OF DEMAND, PRICED
$2 ABOVE THE RANGE AT $19.
WE'RE OUT AT $22, $23 RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE NOT THERE ON VOLUME.
WE'RE FINE TUNING THE PRICE AND
THE DEPTHOF THE BOOK
WE HAVE A WAYS TO GO ON VOLUME,
PRETTY GOOD DEMAND IN THAT
RANGE.
>> GIVE US A SENSE OF WHAT
YOU'RE DOING RIGHT NOW AND DO WE
HAVE ANY IDEA ABOUT THE TIME
IT IS A LITTLE EARLY, BUT GIVE
US A SENSE OF WHAT YOU'RE DOING
RIGHT NOW TO BUILD THAT BOOK AND
HOW IT WORKS.
>> WE HAVE A LOT OF TIME LEFT.
WE'RE NOT IN CRUNCH TIME AT ANY
MODE
BUT RIGHT NOW, WE ARE DISPLAYING
PRICE AND VOLUME AT EACH PRICE
POINT IN THIS RANGE TO ALL THE
ASSET MANAGERS, TO ALL THE BANKS
ON THE SYNDICATE
RIGHT NOW, IT IS JUST REALLY
DISPLAYING VOLUME AND PRICE.
>> AND RIGHT NOW, SALES, WE HAVE
TRADERS BEHIND YOU, FLOOR
TRADERS ALSO STANDING, YELLING
OUT ORDERS TO BUY AND SELL AT
THE SAME TIME.
YOU'RE CONSOLIDATING ALL THAT
INTEREST AROUND THE DIFFERENT
POINTS
>> THEY REALLY CARE ABOUT
ANYTHING IN BETWEEN 22, 23, THE
AMOUNT OF VOLUME OF EACH PRICE
POINT, JUST THE WAY THEY CAN
DISPLAY THAT LIQUIDITY TO THE
CUSTOMERS ON THE PHONE
AND THEN WE GET TO CRUNCH TIME,
THEN THERE ARE CUSTOMERS
PROBABLY WILL REACT TO THE
PRICES AND LIQUIDITY THAT WE
GIVE THEM.
>> WE SAW THIS -- PAGER DUTY,
PAGER DUTIES, PRICE KEPT SLOWLY
MOVING UP AND AT THE TOP, WE SAW
A WHOLE BUNCH OF SELL ORDERS,
PEOPLE WERE SAYING, KAY, YOU
WANT TO BUY IT AT $39, WE'LL BE
HAPPY TO SELL IT AT $39 AND THEN
THE PRICE DROPPED.
IT IS AN AUCTION.
>> IT IS A TRANSPARENT AUCTION
OUR JOB IS TO ADD LIQUIDITY TO
THE BOOK UP AND DOWN, FINE TUNE
THE PRICE, WORK WITH THE
SYNDICATES, THERE IS ALWAYS A
PRICE WHERE CUSTOMERS WOULD SELL
IT AND ALWAYS A PRICE WHERE
CUSTOMERS WOULD BUY IT
THESE DEALS ARE A LOT OF DEMAND.
OUR JOB IS TO FINE TUNE THAT AND
ADVERTISE THAT
>> THANK YOU
STILL DON'T HAVE A PRICE,
SOMETIME AROUND 11:00 A.M.
WE'LL BE DOWN HERE
BACK TO YOU.
>> WE'LL CHECK IN WITH YOU
THROUGHOUT THE HOUR.
MEANTIME, JON FORTT AT THE
NASDAQ MONITORING THE ZOOM IPO
HOW DO THINGS LOOK THERE
>> IT IS HARD TO SAY, CARL,
EXACTLY WHEN THESE THINGS GET
STARTED.
DON'T SEE INDICATIONS YET, THIS
IS PRICED AT $36
YOU WOULDN'T KNOW IT FROM THIS
SHOT, BUT THIS ROOM FILLED OUT,
LOTS OF PEOPLE FROM ZOOM ON THE
OTHER SIDE OF THE CAMERA THERE
AND AS WE TALKED ABOUT, THIS IS
A VERY INTERESTING DAY WITH
PINTEREST THERE AT THE NYSE,
ZOOM AT THE NASDAQ, BOTH
COMPANIES UP AGAINST STIFF
COMPETITION FROM TECH GIANTS
ZOOM HAS BEEN FACING DOWN CISCO,
MICROSOFT, GOOGLE, ADOBE
JUST GROWN EXPLOSIVELY
ALSO MANAGED TO BE PROFITABLE AT
THE SAME TIME.
SO REALLY EAGER TO SEE WHERE
THIS OPENS
I HEAR A LOT ABOUT THE DEMAND
CONTINUING TO BE STRONG AS THEY
CONTINUE TO BUILD OUT THE BOOK
FOR THIS
SO WE'RE GOING TO BE HERE FOR
THE REST OF THE MORNING, EAGER
TO SEE HOW THIS OPENS UP AND
HAVE ERIC ON, THE FOUNDER AND
CEO WITH US COMING UP ON "SQUAWK
ALLEY".
>> JON, BACK IN 2017, VALUED
DOO
ZOOM AT $1 BILLION
RIGHT NOW ABOUT TEN TIMES
GREATER THAN THAT.
WHAT IS YOUR SENSE IN TERMS OF
HOW WE HAVE SEEN THIS VALUATION
SOAR IN LESS THAN TWO YEARS?
>> IT IS PRETTY EXTRAORDINARY.
ON A COUPLE OF COUNTS.
ONE, THEIR GROWTH IS EXPLOSIVE,
ABOVE 100% YEAR OVER YEAR.
THEY HAVE THIS SORT OF MODEL
THAT HAS GOTTEN PEOPLE INTO THE
FUNNEL, BUT THEN ACTUALLY PAYING
ENTERPRISE PAYING FOR THIS
COMMUNICATIONS PLATFORM.
GOT A NUMBER OF INTERESTING
PARTNERSHIPS, OF COURSE, WITH
RESELLERS, ALSO INTEGRATIONS
WITH THE LIKES OF SAY, RING
CENTRAL.
THEY HAVE MANAGED TO BOTH DO
THIS EXPLOSIVE GROWTH, BUT THEN
ALSO PROFITABILITY AT THE SAME
TIME
FOR EXAMPLE, RING CENTRAL HAS
BEEN PUBLIC FOR A LONG TIME.
DOESN'T HAVE EVEN THAT LEVEL OF
PROFITABILITY.
SO RIGHT NOW I THINK WHEN THERE
ARE A NUMBER OF INVESTORS WHO
ARE BOTH INTERESTING EXPLOSIVE
GROWTH AND PERHAPS AS WE SAW
WITH LYFT, WARY ABOUT LOSSES,
ZOOM HAS A STORY THAT FITS VERY
COMFORTABLY RIGHT IN THE SWEET
SPOT OF BOTH OF THOSE THINGS,
GUYS
>> YEAH, OF COURSE, NOW YOU GET
REPORTS, I BELIEVE RICOED
YESTERDAY THAT MICROSOFT
APPROACHED THE COMPANY ABOUT
ACQUIRING IT IN THE PAST
DO YOU THINK THAT'S ADDED TO
SOME OF THE INVESTOR EXCITEMENT
HERE
>> I WOULDN'T DOUBT IT
YOU TAKE A LOOK AT GARDENER'S
MAGIC QUADRANT, A RESEARCH
OUTFIT THAT IS VERY DEEPLY
EMBEDDED IN THE ENTERPRISE AND
THEY HAVE THIS WAY OF MEASURING
BOTH HOW CAPABLE IT IS IN TERMS
OF DELIVERING TECHNOLOGY AND HOW
VISIONARY IS IT IN DELIVERING
TECHNOLOGY
YOU WANT TO BE ON THE UPPER
RIGHT-HAND SIDE OF THAT
QUADRANT, WELL, ZOOM IS THERE.
EVEN AS A SMALL COMPANY, UP
THERE WITH CISCO, WITH
MICROSOFT.
THOSE ARE A COUPLE OF NAMES YOU
WOULD EXPECT TO BE TAKING A
CLOSE LOOK AT ZOOM BOTH IN THE
PAST, PERHAPS IN THE FUTURE.
THE PRICE KEEPS GOING UP, FAIR
TO SAY
>> JON, THANK YOU.
JON GOING TO BE CONTINUING HIS
COVERAGE OF THAT ZOOM IPO,
SPEAKING TO THE CEO ONCE THAT
STOCK BEGINS TO TRADE.
HERE AT THE NEW YORK STOCK
EXCHANGE, WE'RE AWAITING FOR
ZOOM AND PINTEREST RIGHT BEHIND
ME HERE IN TERMS OF THE PIECE
YOU HEARD FROM BOB PISANI,
$22.50 TO $23.50
LET'S TALC MORE ABOUT THE PUBLIC
L
LISTINGS
WE'RE JOINED BY CAMERON ANSARI,
FORMER HEAD OF CORPORATE
DEVELOPMENT AND STRATEGY AT
PINTEREST AND EARLY UBER
INVESTOR VICTOR ORLOFSKY
CAMERON, DO YOU OWN ANY STOCK,
BY THE WAY
>> I DO.
>> EXCITING DAY FOR YOU.
>> MY CO-WORKERS HERE, LIKE A
TRIP DOWN MEMORY LANE.
>> ONCE WE GET PAST DAY ONE AND
THE EXCITEMENT OF THAT, AND
WE'LL SEE WHERE THE STOCK OPENS,
HOW DO YOU BELIEVE INVESTORS ARE
BEST SERVED MEASURING THE
PROGRESS OF THIS COMPANY
IMETRICS.
>> WITH PINTEREST IN PARTICULAR,
I THINK MAU TELLS PART OF THE
STORY.
I THINK ENGAGEMENT AND THE USES
OF THE PLATFORM WHICH ARE REALLY
FOR PEOPLE TO FIND INSPIRATION
AND THINK ABOUT COMMERCIAL
INTENT, PRODUCT ZOFRY, THINGS OF
THAT NATURE, DIFFERENT THAN
OTHER PLATFORMS OUT THERE THAT
ARE PURELY AN MAU FOCUSED STORY.
YOU CAN LOOK AT PINTEREST AND
THINK ABOUT HOW MUCH ARE THEY
GENERATING PERUSER, WHICH IS OUR
AVERAGE, THAT METRIC WILL GO UP
OVER TIME AS THEY GET MORE
MATURE.
>> AND ENGAGEMENT.
YOU LOOK AT THE VALUATION TODAY,
YOU WERE THERE UNTIL 2017,
TOWARDS ONE OF THE LAST ROUNDS,
IT LOOKS LIKE THE MARKET CAP
WILL EXCEED THE LAST ROUND
IS THAT IN YOUR EVALUATION
SOMETHINGING THAT SHOULD BE THE
CASE
>> I CAN'T COMMENT ON THE
VALUATION, THE MARKET WILL DO
WHAT IT DOES
IT HAS BEEN ALL OVER THE PLACE
THIS MORNING
WE LOOK AT IN SIX MONTHS WHEN
ALL OF US IN THIS ROOM, THE
LOCKUP COMES UP AND THE
INVESTORS AND INSIDERS CAN DO
SOMETHING WITH THEIR SHARES AND
WHERE THE STOCK IS TRADING THEN.
TODAY, A GREAT MOMENT FOR THE
COMPANY.
THE VALUATION WILL --
>> YOU MENTIONED LOCKUP.
YOU ANTICIPATE YOU'LL SELL SOME
SHARES WHEN THE LOCKUP COMES
>> WE'LL SEE.
>> I ASSUME IT WAS AN IMPORTANT
PART OF YOUR COMPENSATION.
>> I THINK FOR A LOT OF FOLKS,
IT IS A BIG EVENT, A NICE
MOMENT
SEEING EVERYONE HERE IS
EXCITING, I THINK.
>> VICTOR, IT IS A TALE OF TWO
TECH UNICORNS TODAY.
ONE AT THE NASDAQ, MORE
ENTERPRISE FACING AND WILL BE
VALUED AT ALMOST $10 BILLION
BASED ON THE IPO SHARE PRICE
LAST NIGHT
THE OTHER HERE AT THE STOCK
EXCHANGE, MORE CONSUMER FACING,
PINTEREST.
ALSO VALUED AROUND $10 BILLION
IN TERMS OF WHAT WE HAVE SEEN
WITH TECH IPO PERFORMANCE SO FAR
THIS YEAR, AND HOW INVESTORS ARE
APPROACHING THESE TWO DIFFERENT
PIECES, HOW WOULD YOU EXPECT
THIS TO SHAKE OUT TODAY AND
BEYOND
>> OKAY, YEAH, HI.
YEAH, FIRST OF ALL, I JUST
WANTED TO -- I THINK THEY DID AN
EXCITING JOB
AND EVENTUALLY IF YOU LOOK AT
PINTEREST, AND ZOOM, YOU
WOULDN'T FIND THEM TO BE
SOMETHING SIMILAR, BUT I DO FIND
A LOT OF SIMILARITY IN BOTH
COMPANIES.
THEY BOTH STARTED IN 2011.
AND THEY CHANGED THE WORLD OF
COMMUNICATION.
SO PINTEREST CHANGED THE WORLD,
WE COMMUNICATE WITH BRANDS
AND ZOOM HAS CHANGED THE WORLD
WE COMMUNICATE WITH PEOPLE
AND I THINK THAT'S A LOT TO SAY
ABOUT THE USER EXPERIENCE,
RIGHT?
SO PINTEREST GIVES A UNIQUE USER
EXPERIENCE TO CHOOSE THE PRODUCT
AND TO PIN THE PRODUCT AND BUY
THE PRODUCT.
ZOOM IS REALLY EXCITING TO
COMMUNICATE WITH PEOPLE.
SO YESTERDAY WE HAD A BET WITH
MY WIFE, WHERE TO INVEST TO.
SHE IS A FREQUENT USER OF
PINTEREST.
SHE'S BUYING THROUGH PINTEREST A
LOT AND SHE'S LIKE USING IT ON
AN EVERYDAY BASIS.
SO THAT'S WHAT I DO WITH ZOOM.
I SPEND MY TIME IN THE
CONFERENCE ROOM AND AMONG ALL
COMPANIES I TRY, ZOOM IS FAR THE
BEST IN MY MIND IN TERMS OF
COMMUNICATION.
SO INVEST EACH IN THE COMPANY,
ME AND MY WIFE, IN THE COMPANIES
WE LIKE THE MOST
BUT THAT'S VERY IMPORTANT THING,
RIGHT.
WHY THIS COMPANY DEFERS FROM
OTHERS IS BECAUSE THEY CHANGED
THE USER EXPERIENCE, THEY
CHANGED THE WAY WE THINK ABOUT
THE PRODUCTS, AND THE
COMMUNICATION, RIGHT
SO I AM EXCITED ABOUT HAVING
THIS IPOs.
WANTED TO SAY THANK YOU FOR THE
TEAMS, BOTH TEAMS, THEY WILL
CONTINUE TO INNOVATE AND THERE
IS TONS OF TALENT IN BOTH
COMPANIES.
SO I WOULD ASSUME THEY WILL BE
DOING REALLY GREAT THROUGHOUT
AND THEY WILL BECOME A GREAT
COMPETITOR TO BOTH MEN
ZOOM AND FACEBOOK, TWITTER,
PINTEREST.
>> OKAY.
CAMERON, I FEEL LIKE I'LL BE
ASKING THIS QUESTION A LOT TODAY
AND BEYOND
AS SOMEBODY WHO USED TO WORK AT
PINTEREST AND SO FOCUSED NOW IN
YOUR CURRENT ROLE ON FINANCIAL
TECHNOLOGIES, THE OPPORTUNITY IN
TERMS OF MONETIZING THOSE
MONTHLY ACTIVE USERS ON THE
PLATFORM, SHOPPING, THE
POSSIBILITIES THERE, PAYMENTS,
ET CETERA, HOW WOULD YOU EXPECT
THAT TO PLAY OUT.
>> I THINK THE BIG THING PEOPLE
THINK ABOUT IS E-COMMERCE.
FOLKS ARE COMING TO PINTEREST
WITH AN INTENT TO SHOP AND FIND
PRODUCTS TO POTENTIALLY TRANSACT
ON EVENTUALLY.
HOW IS THIS SITE GOING TO
LEVERAGE THAT AND HAVE LINKS TO
RETAILERS, YOU HAVE SOMETHING
CALLED PRODUCT PINS WHICH HAVE
THE INVENTORY OF ITEMS, THE
PRICING, THE RETAILER WHICH YOU
CAN BUY AND CLICK THROUGH AND
SHOP WITH THAT RETAILER.
TODAY THAT'S IN THE EARLY
STAGES
IT IS A LOT OF OPPORTUNITY
THERE.
BOTH DOMESTICALLY AND SOMETHING
LIKE 94% OF THE REVENUE IS
DOM
DOMESTIC
A MAJOR OPPORTUNITY IN WESTERN
EUROPE AND SOME OF THE MARKETS
IN WHICH PINTEREST HAS A LOT OF
USERS TO MONETIZE THOSE IN
ADVERTISING AND POTENTIAL
E-COMMERCE.
>> WE HAD A DISCUSSION EARLIER
ABOUT THE WAY PINTEREST IS
DIFFERENT FROM OTHER NAMES THAN
SOCIAL
LIABILITIES TO COME FROM BEING
IN SOCIAL.
ARE THERE GUARDRAILS AGAINST
OFFENSIVE CONTENT?
HOW DOES THAT EVEN PLAY IN
SOMETHING LIKE PINTEREST
>> IT ALWAYS HAD THIS DEEP
BELIEF TO KEEP THE SITE SUPER
BRAND SAFE
I SEE THE GUY BEHIND ME WHO LED
THAT DEPARTMENT.
SO IT WAS BOTH MAN AND MACHINE,
WHOLE DIFFERENT DEPARTMENT THAT
MONITORS CONTENT AS WELL AS WE
HAVE ALGORITHMS AND MACHINE
LEARNING THAT DETECTS THINGS
THAT SHOULDN'T BE ON THERE AND
THE WHOLE GOAL IS TO KEEP THE
SITE A PLACE THAT FEELS
FRIENDLY, WARM, INVITING TO
BRANDS AND TO USERS AND DOESN'T
HAVE HATE SPEECH OR
INAPPROPRIATE CONTENT, THINGS
LIKE THAT.
THAT'S A MAJOR PRIORITY.
IT IS THE DISNEY OF CONSUMER
INTERNET SITES
>> YOU RAN CORPORATE
DEVELOPMENT, YOU OVERSAW A LOT
OF DEALS, THEY'LL HAVE A
CURRENCY TO USE NOW.
IS THERE A LOT OF OPPORTUNITY,
DO YOU THINK, FOR PINTEREST IN
TERMS OF FURTHER CONSOLIDATION
OR OTHER THINGS THAT MIGHT BE
OUT THERE THEY WOULD WANT?
>> SURE, LOOK, ONE THING YOU SAW
LAST YEAR, SPOTIFY WENT PUBLIC,
THEY HAVE BEEN ACTIVE IN THE M&A
FIELD.
WE HAVE BEEN ACTIVE FOR THE PAST
SEVERAL YEARS OF PINTEREST
LARGELY SMALLER DEALS, SO ONCE
THERE IS A PUBLIC CURRENCY YOU
CAN USE AND A LOT OF CASH AS
WELL-BEING RAISED IN THE IPO, I
WOULD EXPECT YOU CAN SEE SOME
DEALS IN THE FUTURE, ABSOLUTELY.
>> WE'LL ASK BEN SILBERMANN AS
WELL
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US
>> WHEN WE COME BACK, WE'LL TALK
TO THE CEOs OF BOTH PINTEREST
AND ZOOM AS SOON AS THEIR STOCKS
OPEN FOR TRADE
INTERESTING NEWS OUT OF UNP
TODAY.
RESULTS, A RISE IN QUARTERLY
PROFIT GIVING IT A BOOST
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THE ECONOMY,
PRICING POWER, INTERMODAL RAILS
AND MORE
LOOK AT THE TOP PERFORMING NAMES
ON THE S&P, WHICH IS DOWN JUST
ABOUT 3 POINTS
DOW IS POSITIVE.
BACK IN A MINUTE
From the start, the C-Class
was ahead of its time.
Still, we never stopped
making it stronger.
Faster.
Smarter.
Because to be the best,
is to never ever stop
making it better.
There's never been
a better time
to become part of the
Mercedes-Benz family.
Visit the Mercedes-Benz
Spring Event
before April 30th
for exceptional lease
and financing offers
on the 2019 C 300.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "SQUAWK ON
THE STREET."
VIDEO IMAGES OF BEN SILBERMANN,
CEO AND CO-FOUNDER OF PINTEREST.
HE'LL JOIN US HERE AT POST NINE
AS SOON AS PINTEREST BEGINS
TRADING HERE AT THE NEW YORK
STOCK EXCHANGE
STOCKS WITHIN STRIKING DISTANCE
OF NEW RECORDS, HIGHS OF THE
MORNING AS PINTEREST AND ZOOM
HEADLINE A BIG DAY FOR PUBLIC
DEBUTS AT THE NYSE AND UP TOWN
AT THE NASDAQ.
MIKE SANTOLI AND LESLIE PICKARD
JOINING US NOW
A BIG WEEK IN GENERAL SO FAR FOR
2019 IN TERMS OF IPOs.
>> IT IS
IT IS A BULL MARKET, ACTING LIKE
A BULL MARKET WITH HOPPED UP
IPOs
IF YOU LOOK AT WHAT THE OVERALL
MARKET HAS FAVORED LATELY, IT IS
GROWTH OVER VALUE, IT IS TECH
OVER MOST OTHER INDUSTRIES, AND
IF AN INVESTOR WHO HAS BOTH OF
THOSE BOXES CHECKED OFF CAN GET
A STOCK THAT IS NOT IN HIS OR
HER INDEX AND CAN HAVE THE
CHANCE TO OUTPERFORM, A NEW NAME
THAT HAS BEEN AROUND FOR A
WHILE, I THINK THAT'S WHY YOU'RE
SEEING A RELATIVELY STRONG
INITIAL UPTICK FOR THESE IDEAS.
>> PINTEREST INDICATED TO OPEN
UP 20% HIGHER TODAY, ZOOM UP
MORE THAN 30% HIGHER
IF YOU CAN GET THAT MUCH ALPHA
IN ONE DAY, THAT'S KIND OF THE
MIND SET OF HEDGE FUNDS THAT BUY
INTO THESE THINGS.
NOW, THE CHALLENGE IS HOW LONG
THEY HOLD ON TO IT AFTER THEY
BUY.
IF YOU GET TOO MUCH FLIPPING ON
DAY ONE, YOU CAN SEE A SITUATION
WHERE THE STOCK STARTS TO
PRECIPITOUSLY DECLINE.
>> WHICH IS WHAT WE SAW WITH
LYFT
YOU WERE FOLLOWING THAT
SITUATION.
IS THAT A CONVERSATION THAT IS
BEING HAD ACTIVELY
I IMAGINE IT IS WITH BANKERS AND
OTHER FOLKS INVOLVED IN THE IPOs
YOU'VE BEEN SPEAKING TO.
>> THAT'S A HUGE COMPONENT OF
THE BOOK BUILDING PROCESS.
THEY TAKE A SURVEY OF ALL OF THE
INVESTORS AND HOW MUCH THEY'RE
WILLING TO PAY FOR A CERTAIN
AMOUNT OF SHARES
INVESTORS WILL ALWAYS
OVERPROMISE ON WHAT THEY WANT TO
BUY AND AT WHAT PRICE.
BECAUSE THEY EXPECT TO GET LESS
ALLOCATION THAN WHAT THEY PUT IN
FOR.
THAT SAID, IF YOU'RE THE
UNDERWRITER FOR ANY IPO, YOU
WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT THE --
YOU'RE CREATING A GOOD TRADE-OFF
BETWEEN PRICE AND LONGEVITY WITH
THESE INVESTORS.
MEANING THAT YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
JUST STRETCH FOR THE HIGHEST
PRICE IF YOU GET A BOOK OF
INVESTORS THAT ARE PROBABLY
GOING TO FLIP ON THE FIRST DAY.
>> MIKE, HOW MUCH ARE WE WORRIED
ABOUT THIS TAKING ALL THE OXYGEN
OUT OF THE ROOM AS FAR AS THE
BROADER MARKET IS CONCERNED?
>> I THINK AT THIS STAGE, NOT
TERRIBLY WORRIED
IF ONE THING HAS BEEN ABSENT IN
THE LAST FEW YEARS, IT HAS BEEN
A LOT OF NEW STOCK OFFERINGS, A
LOT OF NEW EQUITY SUPPLY
THERE HAS BEEN MORE STOCK
BROUGHT BACK OUT OF THE MARKET
THAN ISSUED TO THE TUNE OF HALF
A TRILLION A YEAR OVER THE PAST
FEW YEARS.
THESE AMOUNTS THAT ARE BEING
SOLD CERTAINLY $2 BILLION HERE
OR THERE, EVEN IF IT IS 10 FOR
SOME OF THE BIGGER DEALS, THAT
IS NOT JUST GOING TO TIP THE
SUPPLY AND DEMAND BALANCE F YOU
GET OVERAGGRESSIVE ON THE
VALUATIONS, IF YOU HAVE THAT
COLLISION OF PRIVATE COMPANY
VENTURE CAPITAL SILICON VALLEY
MATH WITH PUBLIC MARKET, YOU
KNOW, SCRUTINY AND DISCIPLINE
AND WHAT WE ACTUALLY WANT TO PAY
UP FOR, THAT COULD CREATE A
LITTLE BIT OF STATIC IN HERE
I THINK A BIGGER ISSUE WITH
LYFT
YOU NEEDED TO FIND A PRICE AT
WHICH INVESTORS ARE WILLING TO
SIGN UP FOR YEARS AND YEARS OF
CAPITAL BURN AND MAYBE SOME DAY
DOWN THE ROAD AT THE HORIZON
HAVE A PROFITABLE COMPANY.
>> YOU'VE REMINDED VIEWERS, BUT
PINTEREST'S LOSSES ARE MILD
COMPARED TO LYFT.
>> $63 MILLION FOR THEM.
LYFT WAS CLOSE TO A BILLION
DOLLARS.
UBER, THEIR OPERATING LOSSES ARE
$3 BILLION, THREE TIMES WHAT WE
SAW WITH LYFT.
AT LEAST IN THIS MARKET, IN
2018, STOCKS FOR COMPANIES THAT
HAD NO EARNINGS PERFORMED DOUBLE
AS WELL ON THE FIRST DAY OF
TRADING, UP ABOUT 20% COMPARED
TO COMPANIES THAT DEBUTED
WITHOUT -- OR WITH EARNINGS.
>> YEAH.
GUYS, THANKS FOR JOINING US.
ZOOM IPO IS ZOOMING HIGHER, THAT
INDICATED PRICE OF $52 NOW
VERSUS $36
ONE TO WATCH AS THIS MORNING
UNFOLDS.
>> SPEAKING OF THE IPOs, WE'LL
BE JOINED BY BOTH CEOs
SEPARATELY AFTER THE STOCKS
BEGIN TRADING.
BEN SILBERMANN FROM PINTEREST
AND ERIC YUAN FROM ZOOM.
DOW HANGING ON TO GAINS, JUST
BARELY
N'GOWACK TO 2894
DOT  AY.
It all comes down
to a single defining moment...
...when a plan stops being a
plan and gets set into motion.
Today's Merrill
can help you get there
with the people, tools,
and personalized advice
to help turn your ambitions
into action.
What would you like
the power to do?
♪♪
Feel that?
That's the beat of
global markets,
the rhythm of the world.
But to us,
it's the pace of tomorrow.
With ingenuity,
technologies,
and markets expertise
we create the possible.
And when you do that,
you don't chase
the pace of tomorrow.
You set it.
NASDAQ. REWRITE TOMORROW.
Through the AT&T Network,
Edge-to-Edge Intelligence gives
you the power to see every
corner of your growing business.
From using feedback to
innovate...
To introducing products
faster...
To managing website inventory...
and network bandwidth.
Giving you a nice big edge over
your competition.
That's the power of Edge-to-Edge
Intelligence.
♪♪
>>> WELCOME BACK
NEW INDICATION FOR ZOOM, EVERY
MINUTE IT SEEMS IT GOES HIGHER
5401, PRICED AT $36 A SHARE.
ZOOM WILL OPEN FOR TRADE
IN THE MEANTIME, DOM CHU IS AT
HEADQUARTERS AND HE'S LOOKING AT
INTERNET ETFs FOR OUR ETF
SPOTLIGHT.
>> THAT BIG PINTEREST IPO, AND
ZOOM PUTTINGING IN A LOT MORE OF
THAT ATTENTION ON U.S.-BASED
INTERNET AND SOCIAL MEDIA
COMPANIES THAT ARE PUTTING IN
FOCUS AGAIN THIS IDEA THAT THESE
TRADES ARE BIG AND WHILE WE ARE
TRACKING THE INDIVIDUAL STOCK
MOVES FOR BIG STOCKS LIKE THIS,
THE FACEBOOKS, THE ALPHABETS,
AMAZONS AND NETFLIXES OF THE
WORLD, MANY INVESTORS USE
EXCHANGE TRADED FUNDS TO GAIN
EXPOSURE TO BASKETS OF THE
INTERNET RELATED ISSUES.
SECTOR-BASED FUNDS FOCUSED ON
TECH AND COMMUNICATION SERVICES
HOLD MANY OF THESE NAMES, THERE
ARE OTHER FUNDS THAT ARE MORE
SPECIFIC, MORE HEAVILY EXPOSED
TO SOCIAL MEDIA.
FIRST TRUST DOW JONES INTERNET
FUND, THIS TICKER FDN, $9
BILLION ETF THAT COUNTS AMAZON,
FACEBOOK, NETFLIX AND PAY PAL AS
THE TOP HOLDINGS
THIS PARTICULAR ETF GAINED
AROUND 22% YEAR TO DATE, UP 32%
SINCE THE LOWS BACK ON DECEMBER
24th
IT IS ABOUT 4% AWAY FROM ITS
HIGHS THAT WE SAW IN THE -- OVER
THE 52 WEEK PERIOD
OTHER SMALLER ETF FOCUSED ON
SOCIAL MEDIA OR TELECOM COULD
ALSO AT SOME POINT MAYBE HOLD
SOME OF THE NAMES LIKE PINTEREST
AND ZOOM DEPENDING ON THE
STRATEGIES
STILL, THAT PARTICULAR FUND,
MORGAN, ONE TO WATCH AS WE TALK
ABOUT ALL OF THE INTERNET STOCKS
IN THE CONTEXT OF PINTEREST AND
ZOOM GOING PUBLIC.
BACK OVER TO YOU
>> ABSOLUTELY, DOM, THANK YOU.
WE'RE AWAITING THE FIRST TRADE
AT THE NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE
COMING UP, ONE OF THE MOST
FOLLOWED PINTEREST USERS WITH 13
MILLION STRONG
SHE JOINS US TO DISCUSS THE PLAT
FOREIGN MIN
FORM AND HOW SHE USES IT TO HELP
DRIVE BUSINESS GROWTH.
MORE "SQUAWK ON THE STREET"
AFTER THIS BREAK
Opportunities aren't always
obvious.
Sometimes, they just drop in.
CME Group can help you navigate
risks
and capture opportunities.
We enable you to reach global
markets
and drive forward with broader
possibilities.
CME Group - How the world
advances.
♪
HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN'T GET
HIGH SPEED INTERNET WHERE YOU
LIVE? WELL YOU CAN, WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITE INTERNET WHEREVER YOU
LIVE. HUGHESNET GEN 5 IS FAST.
YOU'LL GET 25MBPS, PLUS BUILT-IN
WI-FI, AND THERE'S NO HARD DATA
LIMITS. SO, WHEREVER YOU LIVE,
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
EVERYTHING YOU LOVE ONLINE.
CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, STAY
INFORMED, WATCH THE LATEST
VIDEOS, AND HELP YOUR KIDS GET
AHEAD. NO WONDER HUGHESNET IS
AMERICA'S NUMBER ONE CHOICE FOR
SATELLITE INTERNET. ACT NOW TO
SAVE BIG WITH OUR LIMITED TIME
OFFER. GET FREE STANDARD
INSTALLATION BY CALLING RIGHT
NOW. SO, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING
FOR? GET HUGHESNET GEN5. TO
ORDER, CALL THE NUMBER ON YOUR
SCREEN. BE SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR
HOME PHONE SERVICE, TOO. CALL
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN
TODAY.
>>> HELLO, EVERYBODY
I'M CONTESSA BREWER WITH YOUR
CNBC NEWS UPDATE AT THIS HOUR.
NORTH KOREA STATE NEWS REPORTS
THE COUNTRY TEST FIRED A NEW
TYPE OF TACTICAL GUIDED WEAPON
IT IS THE COUNTRY'S FIRST SUCH
TEST IN ABOUT SIX MONTHS,
POSSIBLY A SIGN OF ITS
DISPLEASURE WITH THE DEADLOCKED
NUCLEAR TALKS WITH THE UNITED
STATES
A 6.1 MAGNITUDE EARTHQUAKE HIT
TAIWAN CAUSING DAMAGE TO
BUILDINGS IN THE CAPITAL OF
TAIPEI
THE DEPTH WAS SIX MILES ACORDING
TO THE U.S. GEOLOGICAL SURVEY.
THE SUBWAY SYSTEM SUSPENDED
SERVICE.
SCHOOLS ALONG THE EAST COAST
WERE EVACUATED
>>> A HOSPITAL OFFICIAL ON
PORTUGAL'S MADEIRA ISLAND SAYS
AUTHORITIES EXPECT TO IDENTIFY
THE 29 VICTIMS OF A TOUR BUS
CRASH BY SATURDAY.
THE BUS VEERED OFF A ROAD AND
ROLLED DOWN A STEEP HILL LAST
NIGHT.
IT WAS CARRYING MOSTLY GERMAN
TOURISTS
THAT ISLAND IS A POPULAR
EUROPEAN HOLIDAY DESTINATION.
>>> FIREFIGHTERS WERE HONORED AT
THE ELYSEE PALACE.
THEY BATTLED THE FLAMES FOR 14
HOURS BEFORE THEY COULD CONTAIN
IT
THAT'S OUR CNBC NEWS UPDATE AT
THIS HOUR.
BACK TO YOU, CARL.
>> CONTESSA, THANK YOU.
>>> PINTEREST'S FIRST TRADE IS
EXPECTED SOON.
THE VALUATION MOVING HIGHER ON
SOME OF THE EARLY INDICATIONS.
LIKE SNAP, IT MIGHT NOT BE
WIDELY USED BY A CERTAIN
INVESTOR BASE.
TO HELP US DIVE INTO THE SERVICE
AND HOW THEY MAKE MONEY, JOINING
US IS ONE OF PINTEREST'S MOST
FOLLOWED USERS, LOS ANGELES
BASED DESIGNER JOEY CHOI
THANK YOU FOR THE TIME TODAY
APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME
>> HOW LONG HAS IT TAKEN YOU
ASSEMBLE THAT MANY FOLLOWERS
>> I'VE BEEN ON PINTEREST FOR
NINE YEARS SINCE THE VERY
BEGINNING.
AND THE VERY BEGINNING I HAD A
SOCIAL PRESENCE THROUGH BLOG AND
EARLY SOCIAL MEDIA DAYS.
SO OUR FOLLOWING BEGAN TO GROW
AS PINTEREST BECAME MORE USED
WIDELY.
>> YOU WERE ABLE TO GROW YOUR
DESIGN BUSINESS AND YOU WORKED
WITH COMPANIES LIKE MICROSOFT,
TARGET, URBAN.
CAN YOU CHARACTERIZE THEIR LEVEL
OF INTEREST IN YOU BECAUSE OF
WHAT YOU'RE DOING ON PINTEREST
>> THESE DAYS BRANDS ARE LOOKING
TO WORK WITH INFLUENCERS WHO CAN
REACH PEOPLE MULTIPLE DIFFERENT
WAYS
BECAUSE WE HAVE PRODUCTS, A
LIFESTYLE BRAND, PEOPLE WANT TO
SEE HOW YOU CAN BE INSPIRED BY
THOSE THINGS
WE CAN CREATE SOMETHING AND
PINTEREST ALLOWS US TO DO THAT
BY CREATING CONTENT AND SHARING
IT WITH ALL OF OUR FOLLOWERS
>> JOY, I KNOW YOU HAVE
FOOTPRINTS ON TWITTER AND
INSTAGRAM.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE BIGGEST
INFLUENCE YOU HAVE IS ON
PINTEREST.
WHY DO YOU LIKE THIS PLATFORM OR
WHY DO YOU PREFER TO USE THIS
PLATFORM MORE THAN THE OTHERS?
>> WELL, PINTEREST IS SUCH A
GREAT TOOL FOR ME FOR MY TEAM
WHEN WE'RE SHARING IDEAS AND
TRYING TO GET INSPIRATION, AND
ALSO FOR ME, SO NATURAL TO SEE
THINGS THAT I WANT TO DO,
RECIPES, HOME DECOR IDEAS AND
MAYBE SOMETHING I WANT TO
APPROACH IN THE FUTURE, SO THE
PEOPLE FOLLOWING ALONG ARE
LOOKING TO FOLLOW ALONG WITH
THAT AESTHETIC AND INSPIRE THEM.
ME CURE RATING MY OWN FEED HELPS
THEM TO CREATE EXPERIENCES THEY
WANT TO HAVE TOO IN THEIR OWN
LIVES.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK THE COMPANY
NEEDS TO DO NEXT AS A PUBLIC
COMPANY TO ENSURE THAT ITS
GROWTH WILL CONTINUE
>> I THINK THE AMAZING THING
ABOUT PINTEREST GOING PUBLIC IS
THE ABILITY TO GROW AND OFFER
MORE CUSTOMIZATION FOR ITS
USERS.
THEY HAVE ADDED SO MANY FEATURES
OVER THE LAST NINE YEARS, I'VE
BEEN SO THRILLED TO GO ALONG
WITH THAT AND SEE IT AS IT IS
GROWING.
I THINK IT WILL ALLOW THEM TO DO
MORE THINGS FOR THEIR USERS AND
PUT A USE TO IT, CUSTOMIZE PAGES
AND SETTINGS MORE TO THE WAY
PEOPLE WOULD LIKE TO.
>> JOY, I WAS GOING TO DIG INTO
THAT A BIT MORE AND SEE IF THERE
IS ANYTHING YOU WANT TO SEE
BUILT OUT FURTHER AND IMPROVED
UPON.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, I WOULD LOVE TO
BE ABLE TO LOOK AT MY PAGE AND
BE ABLE TO MAKE IT A LITTLE MORE
CUSTOM
CUSTOM HEADERS OR JUST THE WAY
THAT IT LOOKS, CHANGE SOME
COLORS AROUND.
SOMETHING I CAN MAKE IT FEEL A
LITTLE CLOSER TO MY BRAND WHEN
PEOPLE ARE COMING TO IT AND
TIEING IT BACK TO MY MAIN
WEBSITE AS WELL.
>> WE KNOW THE DEMOGRAPHIC SKEWS
HEAVILY FEMALE
I USED TO HEAR NUMBERS LIKE 90%,
BUT I'M TOLD LATELY MORE LIKE
60%.
HOW DO YOU DESCRIBE IT TO PEOPLE
WHO PROBABLY SAY I WOULD NEVER
EVEN BE ON THIS PLATFORM,
DOESN'T SOUND THAT INTERESTING
TO ME.
HOW DO YOU EVANGELIZE FOR IT
>> I WOULD SAY 15 YEARS AGO OR
SO, WHEN I FIRST STARTED MY
BUSINESS, I WAS RIPPING UP PAGES
OF MAGAZINES AND PUTTING IT INTO
A BINDER AN THAT'S HOW I SAVED
MY INSPIRATION, PINTEREST IS THE
ONLINE VERSION OF THAT
TO ME IT IS AN ONLINE SCRAPBOOK
AND THE PLACE WHERE I CAN SAVE
THINS I'M INTERESTED, THE GOALS
I HAVE, IDEAS I WANT TO FOLLOW
AND THINGS I WANT TO DO EITHER
NOW OR IN THE NEAR FUTURE T
MAKES IT EASIER TO GET TO IT
ONLINE.
>> YOU'RE INTERESTED IN BUILDING
OUT YOUR PROFILE AND YOUR
BUSINESS ON PINTEREST.
WOULD YOU INVEST IN THE STOCK?
>> YEAH, I WOULD INVEST IN THE
STOCK.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO?
>> I WILL MAKE DECISIONS VERY
SOON
BUT I HOPE TO.
THANK YOU.
>> REALLY QUICK, WE MENTIONED
NEARLY 13 MILLION FOLLOWERS ON
PINTEREST, ABOUT HALF A MILLION
ON INSTAGRAM
AND I THINK PROBABLY IN THE
80,000 RANGE ON TWITTER.
ARE YOU INTERESTED IN TRYING TO
GROW THOSE OR ARE YOU PUTTING
ALL YOUR RESOURCES INTO GROWING
YOUR PINTEREST FOLLOWING
>> WE'RE MOSTLY FOCUSED ON PIVOT
REST AND INSTAGRAM AS A
VISUAL-BASED COMPANY
FOR ME IT MAKES SENSE TO FOCUS
ON THE PLATFORMS THAT ARE
VISUALLY BASED
THOSE ARE THE MOST VISUALLY
BASED AND THE PLACE WE CAN REACH
OUR AUDIENCE THE STRONGEST.
>> CONGRATULATIONS ON ALL YOUR
SUCCESS.
AND OBVIOUSLY IT IS A HUGE
TESTIMONIAL TO THE POWER OF THE
PLATFORM, WHICH WE'RE WATCHING
CLOSELY TODAY.
JOY, THANK YOU
JOY CHO JOINING US TODAY FROM O
JOY.
THE INDICATIONS ON ZOOM GETTING
INTERESTING AT 56.
THE INITIAL RANGE WAS 28 TO 32
THEN 33 TO 35.
AND WE LOOK TO OPEN 20 BUCKS
HIGHER THAN THAT
>> STRONG GROWTH AND TURNING A
PROFIT, I GUESS.
IT IS BEING SEEN AS A DOUBLE
PREMIUM HERE AT LEAST AHEAD OF
THOSE FIRST TRADES
>> WHEN WE COME BACK, DON'T GO
ANYWHERE
UNP HITTING AN ALL TIME HIGH
THIS MORNING
CEO LANCE FRITZ WILL TALK ABOUT
THE RAILS AND WHAT IS GOING
RIGHT.
WE'RE AWAITING PINTEREST AND
ZOOM
WE'LL TALK TO BOTH CEOs AS THEY
OPEN FOR TRADE
LOTS OF ALL TIME HIGHS TODAY
NAMES LIKE NIKE, ESTEE LAUDER,
PNG, PEPSI, HONEYWELL,
MICROSOFT, VA.
N'GOWAY.IS
So...how many credit cards
did I have after
business school?
Six?
Yeah...that interest
rate was crazy.
Good thing I got a loan
to pay them off faster.
And right before I got engaged.
But now that I'm debt-free,
I can actually contribute
to the wedding.
And go on a honeymoon.
You know... out of state.
Well, this is why I SoFi.
With SoFi's no-fee
personal loans,
consolidate your
credit cards
to get one lower
monthly payment.
consolidate your
credit cards
You should be mad that this is
your daily commute.
You should be mad at people who
forget they're in public.
And you should be mad
at simple things that are
unnecessarily complicated.
But you're not mad,
because you're trading
with E*TRADE,
which isn't complicated.
Their app makes trading
quick and simple
so you can strike
when the time is right.
Don't get mad,
get E*TRADE and start
trading today.
One-millionth order.
Millionth order.
♪
There goes our first big order.
44, 45, 46...
How many of these
did they order?
Ooh, that's hot.
♪
You know, we could sell these.
Nah.
♪
We don't bake.
Opportunity.
What we deliver by delivering.
Internet that puts
you in charge.
Alright boys, time to eat.
That handles anything.
[ crowd cheering ]
That protects
what's important.
And reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
>>> ONE OF WALL STREET'S BIGGEST
ROLLS SAYS THE MARKET RALLY HAS
A LONG WAY TO GO
FIND OUT WHAT HE'S WATCHING ON
TRADINGNATION.CNBC.COM
MORE "SQUAWK ON THE STREET"
COMING UP.
>>> TWO BIG PUBLIC DEBUTS THIS
MORNING.
ONE, OF COURSE, PINTEREST HERE
AT THE NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE
WE ALSO HAVE ZOOM, THE VIDEO
CONFERENCING COMPANY, IT IS NOW
SHOWING AN INDICATION TO OPEN AT
$60.
IT KEEPS MOVING HIGHER
THIS AFTER PRICING AT $36 A
SHARE.
LET'S CHECK IN WITH BERTHA
COOMBS, LIVE AT THE NASDAQ
MARKET SITE WITH MORE.
BERTHA
>> RIGHT NOW WE'RE STILL VERY
MUCH IN THE INITIAL STAGES HERE.
THEY ARE TRYING TO PAIR OFF
BUYER AND SELLERS HERE IN THE
IPO.
THEY PAIRED OFF ABOUT 1.5
MILLION SHARES AT THIS POINT
STILL NO REAL INDICATION EXACTLY
WHEN WE'LL BE OPENING HERE
JPMORGAN AND GOLDMAN SACHS ARE
THE LEAD UNDERWRITER
THIS SAY HIGHLY ANTICIPATED IPO,
ONE OF THOSE TECH UNICORNS THAT
IS ACTUALLY PROFITABLE
ZOOM PROVIDES VIDEO
CONFERENCING, IT COMPETES WITH
THE LIKES OF CISCO AND
MICROSOFT'S SKYPE FOR BUSINESS
HOWEVER, IT IS ONE OF THOSE THAT
A LOT OF FOLKS ON WALL STREET
AND IN SILICON VALLEY HAVE BEEN
WATCHING, REPORTING THAT
MICROSOFT AS RECENTLY AS EARLIER
THIS YEAR TRIED TO BUY ZOOM, BUT
THEY DECIDED TO GO PUBLIC
INSTEAD.
BUT THEY ARE ALSO GETTING SOME
BIG BACKING IN THIS IPO.
TAKE A LOOK.
PEOPLE ARE WAITING FOR THE
OPENING TRADES HERE.
AMONG THE INVESTORS HERE, AT THE
IPO PRICE OF $36 A SHARE IS
SALES FORCE.COM.
SALES FORCE VENTURE WILL BE
TAKING $100 MILLION STAKE IN THE
COMPANY, WHICH IS PROFITABLE AND
WITH THAT, THEY ARE PRICING
HERE, THEY'RE GOING TO BE WELL
ABOVE $10 BILLION IN TERMS OF
VALUATION.
EVEN JUST AT THE PRICING OF $36
A SHARE, IT WAS PUTTING THEM AT
ABOUT 28 TO 30 TIMES THEIR
REVENUES
BUT THIS IS A COMPANY THAT IS
GROWING VERY QUICKLY
IT HAS MORE THAN DOUBLED IN
TERMS OF EARNINGS AND REVENUE
OVER THE LAST COUPLE OF YEARS.
AND, AGAIN, IT IS PROFITABLE
NOT THE ONLY IPO HERE TODAY.
I WANT TO MENTION WE ALSO HAVE
AN IPO THAT ALSO UPSIZED ITS
OFFERING AND ALSO PRICED ABOVE
THE RANGE.
THAT IS GREEN LANE HOLDINGS.
THIS IS A VAPING DISTRIBUTOR,
THEY DISTRIBUTE CANNABIS
SUPPLIES TO NEARLY 10,000 RETAIL
ESTABLISHMENTS IN NORTH AMERICA.
THEY PRICED $17 A SHARE.
OPENED AT ABOUT $29 A SHARE.
AND IS DOING VERY WELL HERE IN
ITS DEBUT.
BUT ALL EYES AT THE MOMENT HERE
ON ZOOM, WE'RE GOING TO KEEP
MONITORING THE SITUATION FOR YOU
AND GIVE YOU AN IDEA OF WHEN WE
THINK WE MIGHT GET THAT OPENING
TRADE.
BACK OVER TO YOU, DAVID.
>> BERTHA, THANK YOU
I'M SURE WE'LL SEE YOU MORE AS
ALL OF THIS UNFOLDS THIS
MORNING.
UNION PACIFIC SURGING, UP MORE
THAN 4% NOW, TRADING AS AN ALL
TIME HIGH ON TODAY'S SESSION
UNP CELEBRATING THE 150th
ANNIVERSARY OF THE
TRANSCONTINENTAL RAILROAD
COMPLETION, A ROUTE THAT THE
COMPANY IS STILL USING TODAY
JOINING US NOW ON OUR FIRST CNBC
INTERVIEW, UNION PACIFIC
CHAIRMAN AND CEO LANCE FRITZ
LANCE, GREAT TO SEE YOU TODAY.
I'M GOING TO JUMP RIGHT INTO IT
HERE
IN TERMS OF THOSE RECORD FIRST
QUARTER FINANCIAL RESULTS, A LOT
OF CATASTROPHIC AND REALLY
DIFFICULT WEATHER THAT IMPACTED
THE RAILROAD LAST QUARTER, LIKE
MANY OTHER COMPANIES WE HAVE
SEEN BEFORE.
YOU SAID HERE IN THE RESULTS
THAT THE UNIFIED PLAN 2020,
WHICH IS THAT LONGER TERM
STRATEGY, THE IMPLEMENTATION OF
PRECISION SCHEDULED RAILROADING
HELPED CREATE A ROBUST NETWORK
ALLOWING YOU TO CONTINUE TO
NORMAL OPERATIONS.
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME THIS
MORNING.
THE WAY THE UNIFIED PLAN 2020
HELPED US RECOVER QUICKLY IS
THAT ESSENTIALLY IT REMOVED WORK
FROM THE NETWORK, WE'RE TOUCHING
CARS FEWER TIMES AND THAT GAVE
US MORE CAPACITY IN OUR
TERMINALS TO HANDLE A SURGE.
AND WE DID ONE OTHER THING THAT
I'M VERY, VERY PROUD OF THE TEAM
FOR THINKING OF AND THAT IS THE
HARDEST PART OF THE NETWORK IS
OUR MANIFEST PART OF THE
NETWORK, SWITCHING CARS AND
TERMINALS AND BUILDING TRAINS
VERSUS OUR BULK PRODUCTS WHICH
TEND TO BE UNIT TRAINS FROM
ORIGIN TO DESTINATION.
AND WHAT WE DID WAS WE FOCUSED
ON RUNNING THE MANIFEST PART OF
THE NETWORK COMPLETELY IN ITS
ENTIRETY TO THE EXTENT WE COULD.
AND AS A RESULT, THAT MOST
DIFFICULT PART OF THE NETWORK
WAS MAINTAINED THROUGH THE
OUTAGE
THE OUTAGE WAS EPIC FOR US
WE HAD OUR EAST/WEST MAIN LINE
SEVERED FOR ALMOST TWO WEEKS, 13
DAYS, AND AS FAR AS ANY OF US
COULD TELL, THAT HASN'T HAPPENED
AT LEAST AS FAR BACK AS WE CAN
SEE, LET'S SAY 50 YEARS AGO.
IT WAS AN EPIC, EPIC WEATHER
ISSUE.
>> WOW
AND CERTAINLY, YOU KNOW, ADDED
TO A LOT OF NOISE IN TERMS OF
DATA AND ECONOMIC METRICS WE
KEEP EYE ON IN FIRST QUARTER
GIVEN THE FACT THAT UNION
PACIFIC TOUCHES JUST ABOUT EVERY
TYPE OF GOOD IN SOME FORM OR
FASHION, TO SOME EXTENT THAT IS
MOVING AROUND THE U.S., WHAT IS
YOUR TAKE MORE BROADLY ON THE
STATE OF THE U.S. ECONOMY NOW?
>> U.S. ECONOMY FEELS PRETTY
GOOD TO US
IF YOU LOOKED AT THE FIRST
QUARTER, SO WE WERE DOWN 2% IN
VOLUME, BUT THE WEATHER IMPACT
ALONE WAS A HANDFUL OF
PERCENTAGE POINTS.
AND IF I THINK ABOUT WHAT THE
QUARTER COULD HAVE BEEN, THE
WEATHER IMPACTED DIRECTLY ARE
ENERGY BUSINESS, IMPACTED OUR
GREEN BUSINESS, IMPACTED SEVERAL
OTHER COMMODITIES, ETHANOL, THE
CAR LOAD BUSINESS TO A DEGREE.
AS WE LOOK FORWARD IN THE
ECONOMY, THE INDUSTRIAL ECONOMY
CONTINUES TO FEEL PRETTY GOOD.
THE GULF COAST INVESTMENT
CONTINUES TO COME ONLINE
WE SEE STRENGTH IN STEEL, WE SEE
STRENGTH IN PLASTICS AND
INDUSTRIAL, THE CONSTRUCTION
PRODUCT MARKETS.
AUTOMOTIVE INDUSTRY LOOKS LIKE
SALES ARE EXPECTED TO BE
SOMETHING LIKE 16.8 MILLION
UNITS FOR THE YEAR
THAT FEELS OKAY.
OUR INTERMODAL PRODUCT BOTH
INTERNATIONAL AND DOMESTIC
SHARES SOME PROMISE.
A LITTLE BIT OF A HEAD WIND IN
DOMESTIC INTERMODAL IN THAT
TRUCKS ARE A LITTLE LOOSER, BUT
OVERALL THE ECONOMY, PEOPLE
CONSUMING THINGS, THAT FEELS
PRETTY GOOD.
I GUESS THE ONE QUESTION MARK WE
HAVE IS ON INTERNATIONAL TRADE
AND ON THAT TOPIC, WE NEED
CONGRESS TO RATIFY U.S. MCA AND
CLOSE THE DEAL WITH CHINA.
ONCE THOSE TWO THINGS ARE IN
HAND, THE ECONOMY WILL FEEL
PRETTY DARN GOOD TO US
>> LANCE THAT WAS MY LAST
QUESTION, YOU KNOW
YOU DO HAVE SOME MACRO BEARS WHO
CONTINUE TO POINT TO CAR LOADS
YEAR ON YEAR
WORRIES ABOUT PAPER AND
CARDBOARD, WORRIES ABOUT
TRUCKING AS YOU POINTED TO
HOW WOULD YOU ADVISE THEM TO
PROCESS SOME OF THE METRICS?
>> YEAH, SO I THINK THE NUMBER
ONE ISSUE FOR US IS OUR UNIFIED
PLAN 2020 IN THE PSR
IMPLEMENTATION IS CREATING A
MORE RELIABLE CONSISTENT SERVICE
PRODUCT.
THERE IS DEMAND OUT THERE THAT
IS NOT YET SHOWING ITSELF TO US
AND WON'T UNTIL WE DEMONSTRATE
THAT CONSISTENT RELIABLE
SERVICE.
AS WE DO THAT, I THINK THERE IS
LOTS OF OPPORTUNITY TO MARKET
FOR US NOT JUST IN TRUCK
CONVERSION, INTO OUR DOMESTIC
AND INTERMODAL PRODUCT, BUT THE
CAR WORLD.
IF I LOOK AT THE BROADER
ECONOMY, CONSUMERS STILL FEEL
PRETTY GOOD, THE JOB MARKET
LOOKS PRETTY GOOD, CONTINUING TO
CONSUME, THE INDUSTRIAL
MARKETPLACE CONTINUES TO LOOK
PRETTY GOOD.
AND THE ONE AREA THAT WE JUST
GOT TO KEEP AN EYE ON AND GET
RIGHT IS THE TRADE
>> YEAH.
TOPIC I'M SURE WE'LL BE SPEAKING
MUCH MORE ABOUT IN THE COMING
DAYS, COMING WEEKS AND COMING
MONTHS
LANCE FRITZ, THANKS SO MUCH FOR
JOINING US TODAY ON THIS BUSY
EARNINGS DAY
SHARES OF UNION PACIFIC UP 4%
RIGHT NOW.
THANK YOU.
>> WE CONTINUE TO TRACK THE TWO
LARGE IPOs, ONE HERE, OF COURSE,
THE NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE,
PINTEREST, ANOTHER AT THE NASDAQ
ZOOM, THE INDICATION FOR WHICH
HAS BEEN MOVING UP UNTIL JUST
MOMENTS AGO WHEN 60 SEEMS TO
HAVE BEEN PERHAPS THE HEIGHT OF
5950 NOW THE NEW INDICATION FOR
THE VIDEO CONFERENCING COMPANY
LESLIE PICKER COVERS CAPITAL
MARKETS FOR US, JOINS US BACK
HERE AT POST NINE.
THEY SEEM TO BE GETTING CLOSER
ON ZOOM.
THIS IS ALSO, ACTUALLY, I SHOULD
SAY PINTEREST BEHIND ME
MAINTAINS SORT OF 23 TO 23.50
FOR A BIT OF TIME AS THEY GET
THE BOOK TOGETHER THERE AS WELL.
>> THEY HAVE BEEN NARROWING THE
RANGE, LOOKING LIKE IT COULD
OPEN IN THE 23s.
THAT WOULD IMPLY A POP OF
UPWARDS OF 20%
FOR ZOOM, IT IS LIKE ABOUT 60%
AT THE OPEN.
IF IT OPENS AT THAT LEVEL, WHICH
IT LOOKS LIKE IT COULD
>> 268 MILLION FULLY DILUTED
SHARES OUTSTANDING
YOU CAN DO THE MATH AT HOME IN
TERMS OF 60 TIMES THAT NUMBER.
IT WILL BE INTERESTING TO SEE
THE MARKET CAP BATTLE HERE
BECAUSE ACTUALLY WE'LL BOTH BE
VERY CLOSE IN TERMS OF OVERALL
SIZE
>> I DON'T THINK A LOT OF PEOPLE
WERE EXPECTING WHEN THESE TWO
COMPANIES WENT OUT AND STARTED
MARKETING THEIR ROAD SHOWS
BANKERS I SPOKE WITH SAID THEY
DID EXPECT ZOOM TO BE SAID THEY
DID EXPECT ZOOM TO BE A WINNER
AND EXPECTED IT TO BE HOT
REGARDLESS OF WHERE THEY PRICED
IT JUST BECAUSE THERE WAS SO
MUCH DEMAND CLAMORING FOR THIS
STOCK.
PINTEREST, INTERESTINGLY, CAME
OUT WITH A CONSERVATIVE
VALUATION.
WHEN YOU COMPARE IT WITH SOME OF
THE OTHER PUBLICLY TRADED PEERS
IN SEARCH AND SOCIAL AS WELL AS
E-COMMERCE IT ACTUALLY DID LOOK
LIKE A PRETTY HIGH VALUATION AT
LAST NIGHT'S PRICING OF $19 A
SHARE.
THAT IMPLIES AN ENTERPRISE VALUE
TO FORWARD REVENUE RATIO OF
ABOUT TEN TIMES, WHICH IS DOUBLE
THAT OF A LOT OF THE BIG SOCIAL
SEARCH E-COMMERCE COMPANIES THAT
WE ARE ALL FAMILIAR WITH.
>> GIVEN THE FACT ESPECIALLY
WITH A NAME LIKE ZOOM, THE
MESSAGE HERE FOR RETAIL
INVESTORS ESPECIALLY GIVEN WHAT
WE DID SEE WITH LYFT
>> IT'S A GREAT QUESTION.
A LOT OF TIMES THE CALCULUS IN
PRICING THESE THINGS IS WHAT IS
THE VARIABLE FOR RETAILER.
IT'S A LOT HARDER TO BE ABLE TO
PREDICT WHAT RETAIL IS GOING TO
DO.
WHEN YOU HAVE A NAME LIKE LYFT,
PINTEREST, UBER, YOU CAN EXPECT
THAT RETAIL WILL COME IN AROUND
THE MARGINS ESPECIALLY ON DAY
ONE AND HELP DRIVE THE STOCK
HIGHER.
OVER THE LONG-TERM RETAIL DOES
GET OUT OF A STOCK THAT SEEMS TO
BE EXPERIENCING SOME MOMENTUM ON
THE DOWNSIDE.
ON DAY ONE YOU CAN TRY AND COUNT
ON THAT.
WITH A COMPANY LIKE ZOOM, IT
ISN'T A BRAND NAME AND IT
DOESN'T HAVE AS MUCH OF A RETAIL
COMPONENTS BUT FROM THE
CONVERSATIONS I HAD YESTERDAY
AND THIS MORNING, IT SAYS THE
BOOK BUILDING PROCESS WAS SO
STRONG FOR ZOOM THEY DID FEEL
COMFORTABLE PRICING WHERE THEY
DID.
>> TYPICALLY, YOU DON'T GET
LARGE ALLOCATION FOR RETAIL FOR
THE ACTUAL IPO ITSELF.
RETAIL IS EXPECTED TO COME IN
AND IF JIM CRAMER WAS SITTING
HERE HE MIGHT SAY DON'T AT LEAST
GIVEN THESE LEVELS.
TEN, 11 TIMES REVENUE IS PRETTY
ASTOUNDING, ALTHOUGH THEY ARE
GROWING THEIR REVENUE BASE OVER
100% A YEAR.
>> EXACTLY.
YOU PAY A PREMIUM FOR GROWTH.
WHEN YOU COMPARE THE TWO
COMPANIES, PINTEREST WAS FOUNDED
IN 2009, YOU'RE LOOKING AT A
DECADE OLD COMPANY.
ZOOM IS A LOT MORE RECENT, 2011
I THINK IT WAS FOUNDED.
CLEARLY MORE IN THE UPTICK STAGE
FOR ZOOM THAN FOR LYFT BUT STILL
VERY NICE TOP LINE GROWTH FOR
THAT COMPANY WHICH IS LARGELY
ADVERTISING BASE WHICH AS WE
KNOW IS VERY COMPETITIVE.
>> ADVERTISING REVENUES IN VERY
MUCH IN VOGUE WHETHER IT'S
PINTEREST OR ZOOM RIGHT NOW.
THANKS, LESLIE.
>>> LET'S GET TO DOMINIC CHU
BACK AT HQ WITH SOME NEWS OUT OF
THE SENATE MAJORITY LEADER, DOM.
>> NEW COMPANIES TOOK VERY OLD
WORLD ONES, SHARES OF TOBACCO
STOCK UNDER PRESSURE AFTER MITCH
McCONNELL ANNOUNCED THAT HE WILL
INTRODUCE LEGISLATION TO RAISE
THE FEDERAL NATIONAL MINIMUM AGE
TO BUY TOBACCO PRODUCTS TO 21
YEARS OLD.
IT CURRENTLY STANDS AT 18.
HE PLANS TO INTRODUCE THAT BILL
WHICH WILL COVER ALL TOBACCO
PRODUCTS INCLUDING eCIGARETTES
AS WELL AS SOME POINT IN THE
NEXT MONTH.
THE TWO DOZEN STATES ARE
CONTEMPLATING SOME OF THAT
SIMILAR LEGISLATION SO SHARES
LIKE ALTRIA ALL MOVING TO THE
DOWNSIDE RECOVERING SLIGHTLY
HERE IN THE EARLY PART OF
TRADING TODAY.
BACK OVER TO YOU, CARL.
>> FASCINATING STEP IN
LEGISLATION.
THANKS, DOM.
>>> LET'S GET BACK TO BOB PISANI
ON THE FLOOR POST-DATE AND CHECK
OUT WHAT THE LATEST IS ON
PINTEREST, BOB.
>> WE TALKING ABOUT PRICING 15
TO 17, CAME IN AT 19 RIGHT NOW
INDICATIONS ARE 23 TO 23.50.
IT'S BEEN THERE FOR A LITTLE
WHILE.
PATTY MURPHY, WHAT CAN YOU TELL
US.
>> WE'RE KALED 23 AND A HALF.
IT LOOKS REALLY GOOD.
THE CUSTOMERS GETTING REALLY
CUSTOMER ON VOLUME.
WE'RE PROBABLY A FEW MINUTES
AWAY FROM CRUNCH TIME AND THEN
RIGHT NOW THE CUSTOMERS ARE
REALLY GETTING COMFORTABLE IN
THAT RANGE.
>> WHEN YOU SAY A FEW MINUTES
AWAY, 15 MINUTES 20RKS MINUTES,
HALF HOUR?
>> TEN TO 15 MINUTES AWAY.
WE'RE GETTING REALLY COMFORTABLE
WITH THE BULK.
WE'RE APPLYING GTS TECHNOLOGY TO
CAPITALIZE AND DO THE DEPTH OF
THE BOOK ON BOTH SIDES.
THE CUSTOMERS ARE REALLY
CRUNCHING TOGETHER IN THIS 23
AND A HALF RANGE AND IT LOOKS
GOOD.
>> BUYERS AND SELLERS ARE BEHIND
YOU SHOUTING OUT ORDERS TO BUY
AND SELL AT THIS POINT.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT THE FACT
THAT IT'S BEEN AROUND 23 FOR A
LITTLE WHILE NOW.
IS THAT AN INDICATION THAT
PEOPLE ARE HAPPY WITH THIS RANGE
OR COULD THAT CHANGE
IMMEDIATELY?
>> IT COULD CHANGE, BUT I THINK
WE'RE REALLY COMFORTABLE.
LISTEN, 25% ABOVE THE DEAL
PRICE, IT'S BEEN HEALTHY.
THE VOLUME IS THERE.
GLENN'S DOING A GOOD JOB OF
TALKING TO THE BROKERS.
HE'S GETTING A LOT OF GOOD
INDICATIONS, RIGHT, GLENN?
>> ABSOLUTELY, YEAH.
>> THEY SEEM REAL COMFORTABLE IN
THIS PRICE RANGE AND, YOU KNOW,
TEXTBOOK PRINT THAT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S COMING UP AND WHAT A GREAT
COMPANY, SO WE'RE PROBABLY ABOUT
15 MINUTES AWAY.
>> THANK YOU.
THE IMPORTANT THING HERE AND I
BROUGHT UP THAT $23 FOR A
REASON.
LAST WEEK WITH PAGERDUTY PRICED
AT 24 STANDING RIGHT HERE AT
THIS TIME, ALL OF A SUDDEN THE
INDICATION FLASHED 37 TO 39
PRICING AND THERE WAS A WAVE OF
SELL ORDERS.
YOU COULD HEAR IT FROM THE FLOOR
COME IN.
WHAT THAT MEANT WAS MORE THAN
50% ABOVE THE PRICE, A LOT OF
PEOPLE WHO WERE HAVING STOCK TO
SELL, HEY, GREAT, YOU WANT IT AT
39, TAKE IT.
AND THE PRICE DROPPED AND IT
OPENED AT $36.
SO, YES THERE'S AN INDICATION
THAT A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE
COMFORTABLE AT 23 BUT IF IT GOES
UP TO SAY 24 OR SO, WE COULD GET
ANOTHER WAVE COME IN AND PRICE
AT 22.
IT REALLY IS A DYNAMIC AUCTION.
THERE ARE PEOPLE JUST STANDING
AROUND WITH STOCK TO BUY AND
SELL AND THEY'RE YELLING AT EACH
OTHER GOING INTO IT.
>> YOU'RE WATCHING PINS, I GOT
TO GET YOUR TAKE ON WHAT'S
HAPPENING AT THE NASDAQ AND
ZOOM
>> THE IMPORTANT THING ABOUT
ZOOM IS VERY SIMPLE HERE.
YOU'VE GOT A COMPANY THAT'S
BRANDS NAME.
PROFITABLE AND PROFITABLE ON A
CASH FLOW BASIS AS WELL AND
YOU'VE GOT A COMPANY THAT'S
MAKING MONEY IN GENERAL, SO I
THINK THAT IS A VERY, VERY
IMPORTANT FACTOR.
IT'S CERTAINLY TRUE PINTEREST IS
LOSING MONEY BUT ONLY A VERY
SMALL AMOUNT OF MONEY,
$50 MILLION A YEAR AND THAT'S A
MAJOR FACTOR AS WELL.
>> WE'LL BE WATCHING 23, 60 ON
ZOOM.
WE'RE WAITING THOSE IPOs WHEN
THEY BEGIN TO TRADE.
WE'LL TALK WITH BOTH CEOs.
DOW HANGING ON TO  PNT52OIS, S&P
DOWN TWO.
DON'T GO AWAY.
I need it to guide this analyst
to customize flood
coverage for this house.
So that this team,
can inform this couple,
that their payment will
arrive faster than this guy.
hey.
♪ ♪ ♪
so whether I'm
processing claims
due to this fine gentleman...
(car engine starting)
or suggesting premiums
for this young lady...
AI can help change
everything at this company.
Expect more from AI.
IBM Watson.
[ "Done Melody" plays ]
♪♪
In big ways and in small,
Bank of America is here
to help you get things done.
What would you like
the power to do?®
♪ Done ♪
>>> GOOD MORNING.
IT IS 8:00 A.M. AT PINTEREST
HEADQUARTERS IN SAN FRANCISCO,