FAMILIAR WITH, DO THE PAPERWORK
AND MAKE SURE SOMEONE CAN SIGN
FOR YOU IN THOSE KINDS OF EVENT.
YOU CAN HAVE A DIGITAL POWER OF
ATTORNEY BECAUSE IT ALLOWS THE
TECH COMPANIES, IF YOU SAY I
NEED ACCESS --
>> TO MY HUSBAND'S OR WIFE'S
CLOUD ACCOUNT, YOU CAN GET IN.
AND I FIND ALSO FROM MY OWN
EXPERIENCE THAT ONE'S OWN POWER
OF ATTORNEY MAY NOT BE
SUFFICIENT AT CERTAIN FINANCIAL
SERVICE COMPANIES THAT REQUIRE
THEIR VERY OWN SPECIFICALLY
WRITTEN ONES.
>> IS THAT TRUE?
>> YES
CHECK WITH YOUR BANK AND
BROKERAGE HOUSE TO MAKE SURE
YOURS COMPLIES WITH THEIR RULES.
>> THANKS FOR WATCHING "POWER
LUNCH.
>>> IT IS THE FINAL HOUR OF
TRADE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ABOUT TO HOLD A
KEY TRADE MEETING WITH HOUSE
REPUBLICANS IN JUST A FEW
MOMENTS.
WE WILL BRING YOU ALL THE
DETAILS.
>>> CARNIVAL SHARES GETTING
CRUSHED AFTER EARNINGS
THE CEO JOINS US.
>>> AND WE'RE ABOUT TO GET A KEY
READING ON HOUSING
KB HOMES REPORTING AFTER THE
BELL
"CLOSING BELL" STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>>> GOOD AFTERNOON AND WELCOME
TO "THE CLOSING BELL."
I'M WILFRED FROST ALONGSIDE SARA
EISEN.
LET'S CHECK IN ON THE MARKETS.
WE HAVE LOST STEAM INTO THE
FINAL HOUR OF TRADE BUT IT'S
STILL A POSITIVE SESSION,
UP 0.4% FOR THE MAJOR INDICES.
S RUSSELL IS 0.8%.
EVERY SECTOR IS POSITIVE, LED
HIGHER BY ENERGY, COMMUNICATION
SERVICES AT THE BOTTOM
>> ALL THE FOCUS LATELY HAS BEEN
ON THE BOND MARKET
COMING UP, FED FUNDS FUTURES,
KEY MARKET, SAYING WE MAY SEE A
RATE CUT FROM THE FED AS EARLY
AS SEPTEMBER
FORMER FED GOVERNOR SARAH BLOOM
RASKIN WILL BE WITH US.
>>> BOND MARKETS APPEAR TO HAVE
STABILIZED FOLLOWING A BIG DROP
FOR THE 10-YEAR AND MIKE SANTOLI
IS HERE WITH MORE.
>> YES, WILF
LOOKING AT WHAT THE BOND MARKET
IS DOING, ESPECIALLY IN THE PAST
WEEK OR SO, YOU LOOK AT ABOUT A
ONE-MONTH CHART OF THE S&P 500
AGAINST THE 10-YEAR TREASURY
YIELD, AND STARTING JUST A FEW
DAYS AGO WHEN THE 10-YEAR YIELD
BROKE DECISIVELY BELOW, IT GOT
STOCKS' ATTENTION.
BEFORE THAT LOW YIELDS, GOOD
CREDIT MARKETS OF BEEN
SUPPORTING STOCK VALUATIONS AND
BEEN BEHIND THIS RALLY
IT GOT DOWN TO A LEVEL THAT
PEOPLE SAID DO WE HAVE TO BE
CONCERNED ABOUT GROWTH
LAST THURSDAY, TREASURY YIELDS
STOPPED FALLING AND WE GOT A
RALLY.
FRIDAY YIELDS KEPT GOING DOWN.
SO THIS SEEMS TO BE THE SEESAW
THAT WE'RE ON RIGHT NOW.
TODAY AS WE MENTIONED, WILF, WE
DID HAVE STABILIZATION IN YIELDS
BUT NOT A DECISIVE LIFT.
THEREFORE, WE HAVE A LITTLE
TENTATIVE RALLY GOING ON RIGHT
NOW.
WHAT'S WORKING IN THIS
ENVIRONMENT IS LONG GROWTH
STOCKS
THE BIG CONSUMER MULTI-DECADE
GROWTH NAMES LIKE NIKE AND
STARBUCKS HITTING NEW HIGHS AS
WELL AS SAFETY DIVIDEND PLAYS.
THE BIG QUESTION NOW IS ARE WE
OVERSHOOTING A LITTLE BIT?
IS IT RIPE FOR REVERSAL?
THERE ARE PEOPLE SAYING THE
YIELD MOVE LOOKS A LITTLE
EXTENDED
YOU SEE BANKS RALLYING TODAY,
PERHAPS ANTICIPATING A LITTLE
BIT OF THE FACT THAT MAYBE
THINGS SHOULD UNWIND.
>> AND OBVIOUSLY GOOD TO SEE THE
BANK REBOUND TODAY
THAT'S NOT BEEN A TREND OF LATE.
THE OTHER TREND OF LATE AS WE
DISCUSSED YESTERDAY IS THAT ODD
BALANCE BETWEEN THE LIKES OF
UTILITIES AND THE LIKES OF THE
BIG TECH STOCKS THAT CONTINUES
AGAIN TODAY.
>> IT DOES CONTINUE TODAY.
SO IT'S NOT THE BANKS BOUNCING
AT THE EXPENSE OF THE OTHER
SECTORS THAT HAD BEEN WORKING
MAYBE IT'S A QUARTER ENDING
ISSUE.
OF COURSE TODAY IS THE LAST DAY
TO BUY BEFORE FUNDS CLOSE THE
BOOKS ON THE QUARTER
SO IT COULD BE PEOPLE JUST
RIDING THE MOMENTUM AND SOME OF
THOSE GOOD GROUPS AND BRACING TO
SEE WHAT THE BOND MARKET DOES
NEXT TO GIVE SOME KIND OF
SIGNAL
>> IS YOUR UPSHOT HERE THAT WHEN
IT COMES TO STOCKS AND ACTING AS
A PRESSURE POINT FOR STOCKS,
IT'S REALLY ALL ABOUT THE SWEET
SPOT THE BONDS HAVE TO BE IN
>> YES
IT'S THE LEVEL AND THE SPEED
WITH WHICH YOU GET THERE
IF IT SEEMS LIKE THERE'S A
BUYING PANIC IN TREASURIES, THAT
SEEMS LIKE A RISK OFF MOVE OR
PEOPLE POSITIONING AGGRESSIVELY.
>> VERY ACCOMMODATIVE CENTRAL
BANK ECONOMY STIMULATES.
>> AND A LOT OF THE TECHNICAL
ANALYSIS WHEN THE YIELD CURVE
INVERTS EVEN THOSE SAY DOWN THE
LINE THIS IS A BAD OMEN.
>> IT'S A LONG LEAD TIME BEFORE
YOU TYPICALLY HAVE A RECESSION
IN THE INTERIM IT GIVES A LIFT
TO CONSUMER DISCRETIONARY AREAS
LIKE HOUSING AND AUTOS.
>> WE'LL SEE WITH KB HOMES
REPORTING AFTER THE BELL
WHAT DOES THIS ALL MEAN AS FED
FUND FUTURES SHOW A RATE CUT AS
EARLY AS SEPTEMBER
JOINING US IS SARAH RASKIN
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> HAPPY TO BE HERE.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE COMING OUT
SAYING A CUT WOULD BE THE NEXT
MOVE RATHER THAN A HIKE.
WHERE DO YOU STANDING AT THE
MOMENT
>> IT'S A REALLY TOUGH CALL AT
THIS POINT, BUT AS YOU SAW,
THERE IS REALLY WEAKENING DATA
COMING IN, PRIMARILY FROM THE
ECB.
YOU SAW THE ECB ACTUALLY JUST
RECENTLY DO SOMETHING THAT
INDICATED THAT IT WAS -- THAT IT
WAS FORESEEING A SLOWDOWN.
TOOK SOME PRETTY DRAMATIC
ACTION
THE FED SO FAR HAS STAYED PUT
AFTER REALLY DOING A U-TURN AND
A MAJOR PAUSE, BUT WEARY NOW AS
TO WHETHER THE FED IS GOING TO
BEGIN DOING SOME CUTS.
>> HOW CLOSELY DOES THE FED
ITSELF PAY ATTENTION TO WHAT THE
MARKET IS FACTORING IN IN TERMS
OF A CUT
>> WELL, THE FED HAS TO TAKE
THAT INTO ACCOUNT, FRANKLY
IT'S IMPORTANT THAT THE FED
REALLY KEEP ITS PULSE ON HOW
MARKETS ARE INDICATING, YOU
KNOW, WHAT THEY ARE FORESEEING
IN TERMS OF WHERE THE ECONOMY IS
GOING.
THERE'S OTHER DATA TOO, OF
COURSE, NOT JUST WHAT IS COMING
IN THROUGH MARKETS, BUT WHAT'S
COMING IN THROUGH REAL ECONOMIC
DATA, SLOWING DEMAND, WHAT
EXPORT/IMPORT NUMBERS ARE
LOOKING LIKE
ALL OF THOSE DATA POINTS ARE
GOING TO BE IMPORTANT AS WELL.
>> THE YIELD STABILIZATION OF
THE LAST COUPLE OF DAYS, DID YOU
THINK THAT MARKS THE LOW OF THE
YIELDS FOR THE NEAR FUTURE
>> HARD TO SAY, WILF
IT IS CERTAINLY ONE INDICATOR
THAT IS POINTING IN A DIRECTION
OF THINGS SLOWING DOWN
THOSE, AS YOU KNOW, HAVE BEEN
INDICATORS THAT HAVE POINTED IN
VERY MANY CASES TO THE ONSET OF
SLOWDOWNS AND RECESSIONS.
>> SO THE FED EXPECTS GROWTH TO
BE 2.1%, WHICH IS LOWER THAN IT
WAS, BUT IT'S NOT TERRIBLE, IT'S
NOT RECESSIONARY
DO YOU THINK ODDS ARE IT'S GOING
TO COME IN BETTER OR WORSE THAT
THAT
>> I HAPPEN TO THINK THAT'S THE
HIGH MARK.
YOU CAN IMAGINE PEOPLE IN THE
WHITE HOUSE MAYBE TRYING TO
THINK OF SOME MORE SUGAR HIGHS
HERE THAT COULD ACTUALLY BOOST
IT
I THINK THAT COULD BE KIND OF
DANGEROUS, IF YOU WANT TO KNOW
THE TRUTH.
THESE KIND OF SHORT-TERM KINDS
OF STIMULUS MEASURES CAN BE
GREAT IN THE SHORT TERM BUT NOT
BE VERY GOOD AT ALL FOR THE LONG
TERM
WE HAVE SEEN THERE'S A DRAG
COMING OUT
IT WAS GREAT FOR A WHILE BUT IT
WAS ONLY GOING TO BE SOMETHING
SHORT TERM AND NOW YOU SEE THAT
IT'S PRETTY MUCH OVER.
>> DO WE KNOW THAT FOR CERTAIN
ALREADY?
COULD THIS BE A FACTOR OF Q1
SLOWDOWN OR ALL SORTS OF
FACTORS, LIKE THE SHUTDOWN, ET
CETERA, ET CETERA.
>> CLEARLY Q1 NUMBERS WERE LOW
IN PART BECAUSE OF THE SHUTDOWN,
BUT THERE IS NOTHING TO SUGGEST
THAT THERE'S MUCH LEFT COMING IN
TERMS OF THE TAX STUFF
IN FACT IF YOU LOOK AT REFUNDS,
REFUNDS COMING IN HAVE BEEN AT
ALL-TIME LOWS.
SO THAT IS A SIGNAL THAT THIS
TAX BILL HAS PRETTY MUCH RUN ITS
COURSE.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE LATEST NOMINEE
TO THE FED BOARD FROM PRESIDENT
TRUMP, STEPHEN MOORE
THERE'S BEEN INTENSE BACKLASH
FROM THE RIGHT AND LEFT IN THE
ECONOMICS WORLD TO THIS
NOMINATION.
>> YES, INDEED
THIS HAS GOT TO BE WATCHED
BECAUSE IF THE FED LOSES
CREDIBILITY BY SEATING PEOPLE
THAT IN ESSENCE ARE MORE
POLITICAL THAN OBJECTIVE, I
THINK YOU RUN SOME BIG RISKS
IT'S ONE THING TO BE PUTTING
YOUR POLITICAL FRIENDS AND
CRONIES WITHIN THE AGENCIES, BUT
TO PUT THEM ON THE BOARD OF THE
CENTRAL BANK IS SOMETHING THAT
IS -- THAT HAS TO BE DONE VERY,
VERY CAUTIOUSLY BECAUSE THE
MOMENT THE FED LOSES
CREDIBILITY, IT'S ALMOST GAME
OVER.
>> HAVING A BROAD RANGE OF VIEWS
ACROSS A COMMITTEE OR A BOARD IS
ALWAYS IMPORTANT IN ANY WALK OF
LIFE
WHAT MAKES YOU SO CONFIDENT THAT
MR. MOORE WOULD TAKE HIS ROLE AS
A POLITICAL ONE AND NOT ONCE IN
POSITION ASSESS THE DATA WITH
HIS WAY OF APPROACHING IT?
>> YOU ARE EXACTLY RIGHT, WILF
IT IS IMPORTANT THAT THE FED NOT
SUCCUMB TO GROUP THINK, THAT IN
ESSENCE YOU HAVE A ROBUST
DISCUSSION OF DIFFERENT
VIEWPOINTS
BUT THE VIEWPOINTS HAVE TO BE
BASED ON DATA.
THEY HAVE TO BE BASED ON AN
ABILITY TO ANALYZE AS
OBJECTIVELY AS POSSIBLE THE DATA
COMING FORTH
AND BY MANY ACCOUNTS, THAT IS
NOT MR. MOORE'S STRONG POINT
THE ANALYSIS OF DATA IS
SOMETHING THAT IS CRITICAL FOR
THE FED TO BE BOTH INDEPENDENT
AND TO BE -- TO BE MAKING MOVES
AND COMMUNICATING MOVES THAT ARE
CREDIBLE.
>> SO WE'RE JUST ACTUALLY
GETTING NEWS ON THE WIRES ON
THIS
FROM SENATOR CHUCK SCHUMER
SAYING HERE ON CAPITOL HILL, FED
NOMINEE STEPHEN MOORE IS ONE OF
THE REASONS FOR THE LARGE
DEFICIT.
ALL HE WANTS TO DO IS CUT TAXES,
CUT TAXES, CUT TAXES
THAT'S NOT WHAT THE FED REALLY
DOES, AS YOU KNOW, SO HOW MUCH
POWER WOULD HE ULTIMATELY HAVE
IF HE GETS THROUGH ON THE SENATE
CONFIRMATION
JUST HOW BIG OF A DEAL IF IT'S
ONE SORT OF TRUMP LOYALIST ON
THE FED BOARD?
>> YEAH, I KNOW THE ARGUMENT
I KNOW IT'S TEMPTING TO SAY, OH,
WHAT IS JUST ONE VOICE, LET ONE
VOICE THROUGH THAT MIGHT BE JUST
A WASTED SEAT.
THESE ARE IMPORTANT TIMES.
THE WORK THAT THE FOMC DOES HAS
TO BE CREDIBLE
EVERY VOICE MATTERS.
I WOULD NOT START DOWN THE PATH
OF SAYING, YOU KNOW, IT'S OKAY
TO GET SORT OF ONE SORT OF
POLITICAL PUNDIT IN THERE.
I THINK THIS IS -- THIS IS
DANGEROUS.
THIS NEEDS TO BE LOOKED AT QUITE
CAREFULLY.
>> DANGEROUS IS A STRONG WORD,
SARAH.
>> YEAH.
>> JUST LOOK AT SOME OF THE
ECONOMIC APPOINTMENTS HE'S MADE,
THE PRESIDENT HAS MADE
THERE WAS A LOT OF CRITICISM
COMING IN FOR THE LIKES OF
SECRETARY MNUCHIN, FOR THE LIKES
OF GARY COHN AND LARRY KUDLOW.
ARE ALL OF THOSE PEOPLE WHO YOU
THINK HAVE FARED POORLY IN THEIR
JOB?
DID YOU CRITICIZE ANY OF THOSE
COMING INTO IT
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK WHAT WE'VE
GOT TO DO IS DISTINGUISH THE
FED.
THAT IS SOMETHING.
>> THE FED IS SACRED
>> THE FED IS IN ESSENCE
INDEPENDENT.
FOR THAT REASON IT HAS TO DO
WHATEVER CAN BE DONE TO MAINTAIN
ITS INDEPENDENCE
I THINK IT'S INCUMBENT UPON THE
SENATORS WHEN THEY DO OVERSIGHT
TO DO THIS VERY, VERY CAREFULLY.
THIS IS WHY OVERSIGHT MATTERS.
AND WE -- YOU KNOW, I THINK IT'S
IMPORTANT THAT THE OVERSIGHT BE
DONE WELL.
THESE FED SEATS DO MATTER.
>> SARAH BLOOM RASKIN, THANK
YOU.
GOOD TO SEE YOU AS ALWAYS.
>> WE WANT MR. MOORE TO COME
BACK AND JOIN US
HE WAS HERE, WHAT, A MONTH AGO
>> YEAH, HE WAS GOING TO COME
ON
YOU KNOW, HE'S GOING GO THROUGH
A TOUGH NOMINATION PROCESS
WE WOULD LIKE TO HEAR FROM HIM.
>>> STILL TO COME, SHARES OF
CARNIVAL SINKING TODAY AFTER THE
COMPANY CUT ITS FULL-YEAR
OUTLOOK.
WE WILL SPEAK WITH CEO ARNOLD
DONALD ABOUT THE HEADWINDS
FACING HIS INDUSTRY.
>>> AND UP NEXT, RICK WELTS
JOINS US TO TALK ABOUT THE STATE
OF THE NBA, HIS NEW TEAM'S
PRIVATELY FUNDED BILLION DOLLAR
ARENA.
WE'RE BACK IN COLEF
NUS.A UP O
>>> WELCOME BACK
AS CHINA TRADE TALKS DOMINATE
THE HEADLINES, PRESIDENT TRUMP
IS MEETING WITH HOUSE
REPUBLICANS IN A FEW MINUTES TO
DISCUSS ANOTHER TRADE DEAL
LET'S GET TO KAYLA TAUSCHE WITH
THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: THE FOUR MONTHS
SINCE THE THREE COUNTRIES SIGNED
THIS DEAL, THE WHITE HOUSE HAS
BEEN STRATEGIZING BEHIND CLOSED
DOORS WITH REPUBLICANS TO FIGURE
OUT WHAT IS GOING TO BE A
DELICATE PATH TO PASSAGE IN THE
COMING MONTHS.
THE WHITE HOUSE HOSTED SENATE
REPUBLICANS A COUPLE OF WEEKS
AGO AND TODAY IN JUST A COUPLE
OF MINUTES THE PRESIDENT WILL BE
MEETING WITH HOUSE REPUBLICANS
TO TALK ABOUT SOME OF THE
CONCERNS THAT THE PARTY HAS
ABOUT ELEMENTS OF THE DEAL THAT
WERE INSERTED TO WIN OVER
DEMOCRATS BUT ARE GIVING SOME
REPUBLICANS HEARTBURN AND VICE
VERSA.
YOU HAVE STEVE SCALISE, THE MAY
NOERT WHIP TO TALK ABOUT HOW
VOTES WILL BE COUNTED.
YOU HAVE KEVIN BRADY, FORMERLY
CHAIRMAN, NOW RANKING MEMBER
AND THEN YOU HAVE
REPRESENTATIVES FROM STATES LIKE
WASHINGTON AND TEXAS, SOME OF
THE MOST TRADE DEPENDENT STATES
WHERE THE NEW NAFTA DEAL IS
CONCERNED.
THE OUTREACH HAS BEEN FAR AND
WIDE
EVEN THOUGH THE WHITE HOUSE HAS
BEEN TALKING A LOT WITH
REPUBLICANS, TRUMP'S TOP TRADE
OFFICIAL HAS ALSO BEEN
FRATERNIZING WITH DEMOCRATS TO
SEE WHERE THEY ARE AND TO MAKE
SURE THEY KNOW ABOUT CERTAIN
LABOR AND ENVIRONMENTALLY
FRIENDLY PORTIONS OF THIS DEAL
AMBASSADOR LIGHTHIZER HAS MET
WITH THE ENTIRETY OF THE HOUSE
DEMOCRATIC CONFERENCE.
HE'S MET WITH THE WAYS AND MEANS
COMMITTEE.
HE'S MET WITH THE BLUE DOG
DEMOCRATS AND THE HISPANIC
CAUCUS
SO YOU CAN SEE THAT THE OUTREACH
ON THIS DEAL HAS BEEN VAST, IT'S
BEEN BIPARTISAN, IT'S BEEN ON
BOTH SIDES OF THE AISLE, AND
IT'S GOING TO RAMP UP IN COMING
MONTHS, GUYS
THE UNOFFICIAL DEADLINE FOR THE
ADMINISTRATION TO GET THIS
PASSED IS THE BEGINNING OF
AUGUST WHEN CONGRESS IS GOING TO
GO OUT FOR A MULTI-WEEK BREAK.
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THAT, IT'S
FULL-FLEDGED CAMPAIGN SEASON.
>> KAYLA, IF THEY DON'T
SUCCESSFULLY SELL IT, DOES THAT
MEAN WE'LL HEAR THE PRESIDENT
THREATEN TO PULL OUT OF NAFTA
AGAIN?
>> IT'S SOMETHING THAT SENATE
REPUBLICANS SPECIFICALLY HAVE
ASKED THE PRESIDENT NOT TO DO.
IT'S UNCLEAR WHERE THAT SPECIFIC
STRATEGY STANDS.
THE EXPECTATION IS THAT THEY CAN
GET THE VOTES OR THEY BELIEVE
THEY CAN GET THE VOTES FOR THIS
DEAL AND THAT WON'T BE AN
OPTION
REMEMBER, THERE ARE TWO OTHER
CUP TREES WHO HAVE TO RATIFY
THIS DEAL TOO SO THE U.S. CAN'T
NECESSARILY MAKE WHOLESALE
CHANGES TO IT IN ORDER TO GET
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS ONBOARD.
SO THE DEAL THAT'S ON THE TABLE
IS THE DEAL THAT'S PRETTY MUCH
GOING TO BE VOTED ON.
>> HOW MUCH FOCUS IS THIS TAKING
OFF CHINA TALKS, KAYLA
>> Reporter: WELL, I THINK THE
IDEA HERE, WILF, IN TERMS OF
TIMELINE AND BANDWIDTH AT THE
OFFICE OF THE U.S. TRADE
REPRESENTATIVE IS THAT THERE'S A
DESIRE TO GET CHINA WRAPPED UP
IN THE NEXT MONTH OR SO BECAUSE
THE EXPECTATION IS THAT IT'S
GOING TO BE A FULL FORCE EFFORT
AFTER THAT, FULL-COURT PRESS ON
USMCA.
EVEN THOUGH THERE ARE DIFFERENT
TEAMS AT USTR NEGOTIATING USMCA
VERSUS CHINA, A LOT OF THE WHITE
HOUSE STAFF IS OVERLAPPED THERE
ON THE TRADE TEAM.
SO CERTAINLY IT IS TAKING TIME
AWAY -- CHINA IS TAKING TIME
AWAY FROM USMCA AND VICE VERSA
IF YOU GET ONE OF THOSE
SITUATIONS SETTLED, IT DOES
ALLOW YOU TO PIVOT AND TALK
ABOUT THE OTHER.
>> KAYLA, THANK YOU.
>> Reporter: SURE.
>>> SWITCHING GEARS, STARTING
THIS FALL THE GOLDEN STATE
WARRIORS WILL HAVE A NEW HOME.
MOVING ACROSS THE BAY FROM
OAKLAND TO THE BRAND NEW CHASE
CENTER IN SAN FRANCISCO.
CHASE CENTER AND THE SURROUNDING
DISTRICT COVERS ABOUT 11 ACRES,
HAS 500,000 SQUARE FEET OF
OFFICE SPACE
JOINING US NOW TO TALK ABOUT THE
DEVELOPMENT AND ITS ECONOMIC
IMPACT ON THE GOLDEN STATE
WARRIORS IS THE WARRIORS
PRESIDENT, RICK WELTS.
WELCOME.
>> THANK YOU
THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> SO FIRST FULLY PRIVATELY
FUNDED STADIUM
HOW DID THAT COME TOGETHER
WHAT'S THE SIGNIFICANCE OF IT?
>> WE MADE THE DECISION THAT WE
WANTED TO BUILD AN ARENA IN SAN
FRANCISCO.
PART OF THE DEAL WHEN YOU WANT
TO DO THAT IS THERE WOULD BE NO
PUBLIC MONEY
SO IT'S A HEAVY LIFT
IT HASN'T BEEN DONE IN DECADES
I WOULDN'T RECOMMEND IT AS A
FORMULA.
A FEW HUNDRED MILLION DOLLARS
WOULD BE REALLY NICE TO BUILD
ONE OF THESE BUT WE KNEW IT AT
THE OUTSET AND WE'RE CLOSE TO
THE FINISH LINE.
>> AND THE PARTNERSHIP WITH
CHASE AS WELL LEADS TO ANOTHER
INITIATIVE, WHICH IS YOU WANT
THIS TO BE A CASHLESS STADIUM
ULTIMATELY.
>> OBVIOUSLY PAYMENT SYSTEMS ARE
AN IMPORTANT PART OF CHASE'S
BUSINESS
THEIR EXPERIENCE REALLY HERE
WITH MADISON SQUARE GARDEN IN
NEW YORK AND THEIR EXPERIENCE IN
TREATING CUSTOMERS IN ARENAS IS
SECOND TO NONE, SO WE'VE BEEN
ABLE TO LEVERAGE OFF OF THAT
EXPERTISE.
WE THINK WE HAVE EXCITING THINGS
TO COME.
>> HOW ARE THE FANS DEALING WITH
IT
BIG MOVE FROM OAKLAND.
YOU'VE HAD DIEHARD FANDS DURING
THE WARRIORS TREMENDOUS RIDE.
>> WE SPENT THIS YEAR
CELEBRATING OUR 47 YEARS IN
OAKLAND.
70% OF OUR SEASON TICKET HOLDERS
HAVE DECIDED TO COME WITH US AS
SEASON TICKET HOLDERS IN SAN
FRANCISCO.
WE LOVE THAT BUILDING, IT'S
OLDER THAN MADISON SQUARE
GARDEN
WE NEEDED A DIFFERENT FACILITY
TO JN RATE THE KIND OF REVENUES
WE NEEDED TO BE A COMPETITIVE
CHAMPIONSHIP TEAM.
>> WHAT HAVE YOU GUYS IN THE NBA
MORE BROADLY GOT RIGHT
LAST YEAR IT WAS THE RECORD
FOURTH YEAR IN A ROW THAT
ATTENDANCES ROSE
THE STREAMING SERVICE, 63%
GROWTH
TOTAL REVENUE INCREASED 25%.
WHAT'S THE NBA GOT RIGHT THAT
PERHAPS SOME OF THE OTHER SPORTS
HAVEN'T CONSISTENTLY DONE IN THE
LAST FOUR OR FIVE YEARS IN A
ROW?
>> I THINK WE HAVE EXTRAORDINARY
LEADERSHIP
ADAM SILVER HAS DONE AN AMAZING
JOB AS COMMISSIONER.
I THINK WE'RE TOUCHING SOMETHING
SOCIALLY WITH OUR AUDIENCE
I THINK IF YOU REALLY LOOK AT
THE SOCIAL MEDIA STATS AND LOOK
AT WHERE OUR AUDIENCE IS, WE'RE
LOOKING AT THAT REALLY COVETED
YOUNGER DEMOGRAPHIC WHO'S REALLY
RESONATING WITH THE
PERSONALITIES OF THE PLAYERS AND
THE TEAMS OF THE NBA
THAT AND THE FACT THAT I THINK
OUR INTERNATIONAL PLAY OVER TIME
IS GOING TO REALLY BE WHAT
SEPARATES US FROM THE OTHER
AMERICAN SPORTS LEAGUES.
WE REALLY DO HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY
TO TAKE THIS SPORT INTERNATIONAL
LOW IN WAYS THAT I THINK
FOOTBALL AND BASEBALL WON'T HAVE
THAT OPPORTUNITY.
>> I'VE SEEN THAT FIRSTHAND WITH
THE SNEAKERS BUSINESS.
ON A MORE LOCAL LEVEL, THOUGH,
HOW MUCH IS THIS THE TEAM OF
SILICON VALLEY
HOW IMPORTANT IS IT TO THE DNA
>> INCREDIBLY IMPORTANT.
I THINK LONG TERM IT'S A BIG
PART OF OUR PERSONALITY, AND A
BIG POINT OF WHY PLAYERS AT SOME
POINT IN THEIR CAREERS HAVE AN
OPPORTUNITY TO PLAY WHEREVER
THEY WANT, SEE SILICON VALLEY
AND THE WARRIORS AS AN EXCITING
PLACE.
BECAUSE OF WHO THEY ARE, THEY
CAN INTERACT WITH EXECUTIVES IN
SILICON VALLEY AND SOME START TO
BE INVESTORS.
>> ON THAT POINT, BEING
INVESTORS FROM THE PLAYERS
CLEARLY STEPH CURRY IS A PIONEER
GETTING INVOLVED IN THE VR
WORLD.
BUT DOES THAT RUB OFF BECAUSE OF
HIM AND HIS LEADERSHIP BUT ALSO
WHERE YOU ARE BASED?
>> I WOULD SAY EVEN MORON DRAY
IGUODALA, KEVIN DURANT, HAVE
TAKEN IT UPON THEMSELVES TO
LEARN ABOUT THESE BUSINESSES AND
LEARN HOW TO INVEST.
I THINK YOU'LL SEE MORE AND MORE
NBA PLAYERS DOING THE SAME
THING.
>> IN TERMS -- IN TERMS OF THE
SOCIAL MEDIA ASPECT, HOW HAS
THAT CHANGED THE NATURE OF THE
FANS' INTERACTION BUT ALSO FOR
THE PLAYERS.
ARE THERE AREAS WHERE YOU REGRET
THE LEVEL WITH WHICH THE PLAYERS
GET INVOLVED
>> THERE'S NO TURNING BACK
THIS IS HOW PLAYERS ACROSS THE
LEGAL INTERACT WITH EACH OTHER
50 YEARS AGO PLAYERS ON ONE TEAM
NEVER KNEW PLAYERS ON ANOTHER
TEAM, AND NOW THEY'RE FRIENDS.
IT DOES CHANGE THE DYNAMIC
IT CHANGES HOW TEAMS ARE FORMED,
HOW THEY THINK ABOUT WHERE THEY
WANT TO PLAY
SO I THINK IT'S BEEN A REALLY,
REALLY BIG FACTOR.
>> THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
YOU BUT THERE'S BEEN AN ODD
STORY ABOUT BASKETBALL IN THE
NEWS THIS WEEK WITH MICHAEL
AVENATTI BEING CHARGED WITH
EXTORTING NIKE, ALL CENTERING
AROUND THE AMATEUR LEAGUE AND
COACHES BEING PAID FOR BRIBERY
HOW BIG A PART OF THE SPORT DO
YOU THINK THIS IS THAT
BASKETBALL HAS TO OVERCOME
>> I THINK WE STILL HAVE THINGS
TO CLEAN UP.
THE NBA,THE PLAYERS ASSOCIATION,
THE NCAA, ARE HAVING SUBSTANTIVE
CONVERSATIONS ABOUT HOW TO
CHANGE THE SYSTEMS SO IT SERVES
THE STUDENT ATHLETE BETTER
RIGHT NOW THE THINGS WE'RE DOING
DON'T REALLY WORK.
THE ONE-AND-DONE ISN'T WORKING
GREAT FOR THE COLLEGES OR THE
NBA.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A BETTER WAY
TO DO IT THAT TREATS THE
STUDENTS LIKE STUDENT ATHLETES
AND GIVES THEM BETTER
PREPARATION FOR THEIR CAREERS.
>> DOES THAT RAISE THE BAR NOW
OF EXPECTATION
WHAT IS NECESSARY?
WHAT IS A BARE MINIMUM FOR THE
NEXT THREE OR FOUR SEASONS
>> WHO WOULDN'T WANT THAT KIND
OF PRESSURE?
WOULD WE RATHER NOT HAVE BEEN TO
THE FINALS FOUR YEARS IN A ROW
I DON'T THINK SO
OR WON THREE CHAMPIONSHIPS
WE LIKE WHERE WE ARE RIGHT NOW.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH, RICK.
>> THANK YOU
>>> STILL TO COME ON THE SHOW,
DESPITE INCREASED CHATTER ABOUT
A RATE CUT, ONE STRATEGIST STILL
SAYS THE FED COULD ACTUALLY
RAISE RATES IN THE SECOND HALF
OF THE YEAR.
SHE WILL EXPLAIN WHY, COMING UP.
>>> PLUS NEW DATA OUT TODAY
POINTING TO A BIG SLOWDOWN IN HS
USG AR
KB HOMES RELEASES EARNINGS AFTER
THE BELL
WE'RE BACK IN A COUPLE
This is Decision Tech.
It's screening technology
that helps you find a stock
based on what's trending
or an investing goal.
It's real-time insights
and information,
in your own customized view
of the market.
It's smarter
trading technology,
for smarter trading decisions.
And it's only from Fidelity.
Open an account
with no minimums today.
>>> STILL AHEAD, PURDUE PHARMA
REACHING A SETTLEMENT OVER ITS
OPIOID DRUG BUT IT'S FACING
FI1500
LAWSUITS
WHAT IT MEANS FOR THE COMPANY
AND THE BILLIONAIRE FAMILY
BEHIND IT.
>>> AFTER THE BREAK, CARNIVAL
STOCK IS DOWN MORE THAN 20% IN
THE PAST YEAR FALLING AGAIN
TODAY HARD AFTER CUTTING ITS
OUTLOOK.
ARNO DALJOS  TLDOND INUSO TALK
ABOUT THE HEADWINDS FACING THAT
INDUSTRY
♪♪
♪Hold on, I'm comin'♪
♪Hold On
Don't you worry,♪
♪I'm comin'♪
♪Here we come,
Hold on♪
♪We're about to save you
I'm comin', yeah♪
♪Hold On
Don't you worry,♪
♪I'm comin'♪
You're turning onto the
street
when you barely
clip a passing car.
Minor accident
—no big deal, right?
Wrong. Your insurance
company is gonna raise
your rate after the other
car got a scratch so small
you coulda fixed
it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that
pen and use it to sign up
with a different
insurance company.
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because of
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>>> WELCOME BACK TO CLOSING
BELL
WE'RE CERTAINLY OFF THE HIGHS OF
THE DAY.
S&P AT ONE POINT WAS UP 31
POINTS, BUT STILL MOSTLY HIGHER
IN TERMS OF SECTORS WITHIN THE
OVERALL MARKET
ACTUALLY EVERYBODY IS UP RIGHT
NOW.
ENERGY IS IN THE LEAD.
CONSUMER STAPLES, FINANCIALS,
UTILITIES ALL GOING STRONG
THAT COMMUNICATION SERVICES
SECTOR IS THE ONE THAT KEEPS
POPPING BACK IN AND OUT OF
POSITIVE AND NEGATIVE TERRITORY.
OVERALL IT'S A PRETTY BROAD
RALLY, EVEN THOUGH IT'S OFF THE
HIGHS.
>>> CONTINUING WITH A CNBC NEWS
UPDATE WITH SUE HERERA.
>> HELLO, EVERYONE
HERE'S WHAT'S HAPPENING AT THIS
HOUR
ISRAELI PRIME MINISTER BENJAMIN
NETANYAHU AFTER ISRAELI JETS
POUNDED HAMAS-RELATED SITES
OVERNIGHT.
HE CUT SHORT HIS VISIT TO THE
U.S. AFTER A ROCKET FIRED FROM
GAZA STRUCK A HOUSE IN CENTRAL
ISRAEL
>> NOW, I'M JUST COMING FROM A
MEETING WITH OUR CHIEF OF STAFF
AND OUR SENIOR COMMAND
I CAN TELL YOU WE ARE PREPARED
TO DO A LOT MORE
WE WILL DO WHAT IS NECESSARY TO
DEFEND OUR PEOPLE AND TO DEFEND
OUR STATE.
>> RUSSIAN PRESIDENT PUTIN
MEETING WITH THE LEBANESE
PRESIDENT IN MOSCOW WHO
EXPRESSED CONCERN OVER THE U.S.
ANNOUNCEMENT THAT IT RECOGNIZED
THE GOLAN HEIGHTS AS PART OF
ISRAEL
HE SAID THAT RECOGNITION
UNDERMINED THE RULES OF
INTERNATIONAL LAW.
>>> AND THE EUROPEAN PARLIAMENT
OVERWHELMINGLY APPROVING A
MEASURE TO ABOLISH THE TWICE
YEARLY TIME CHANGE BY THE YEAR
2021 BUT LAWMAKERS HAVEN'T
DECIDED WHETHER SUMMER OR
WINTERTIME SHOULD BE ADOPTED AS
THE STANDARD TIME.
MORE NEGOTIATIONS TO FOLLOW, I'M
SURE
AND LOTS OF DISCUSSION
THAT'S THE NEWS UPDATE THIS
HOUR
SARA, WILF, BACK DOWN TO YOU.
>> I'M JEALOUS OF THAT.
>> THE ONLY THING I'VE THOUGHT
THEY SHOULD DO, THOUGH, IS WHEN
YOU LOSE AN HOUR OF SLEEP, DO IT
AT THE WEEKEND
WHEN YOU'VE GAINED ONE, DO IT IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE WEEK.
>> IT'S LIKE THE WHOLE CONCEPT
IS STUPID.
>> WHY
IT'S SO GREAT WHEN IT STAYS
LIGHT LONGER AND IT'S NOT SO
DEPRESSING.
>> YOU HAVE A BABY AND
EVERYTHING IS SCHEDULED AN D
RIDGEMENTED AROUND BABIES
SLEEPING AND EATING, GET BACK TO
ME.
>> I LOVE THE DEBATE STARTING
NOW TO HAVE A CHANGE IN 2021.
>> EUROPEAN PARLIAMENT TACKLING
ALL THE KEY ISSUES.
>>> ROUGH DAY FOR CARNIVAL
STOCK.
DOWN ALMOST 9% DESPITE REPORTING
IT BEAT ON REVENUE AND EARNINGS
EARLIER TODAY.
THE STOCK PLUNGED AFTER THE
CRUISE SHIP COMPANY DID CUT
FULL-YEAR FORECASTS.
ALSO WARNED A LITTLE BIT ON
EUROPE.
>> WE SHOULD ASK ARNOLD, THEY
MUST GO THROUGH A LOT OF TIME
CHANGES.
MAYBE HE'S GOT A VIEW ON THIS.
>> MAYBE HE DOES
FIRST, ARNOLD, WELCOME
I'D LIKE TO HEAR MORE ABOUT THE
MOVE IN YOUR STOCK PRICE TODAY
AND WHAT WAS SO SURPRISINGLY
DISAPPOINTING.
WHAT HAPPENED HERE
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, IT WAS
DISAPPOINTING.
WE HAD A BEAT FOR THE QUARTER,
AS YOU MENTIONED
WE'VE GOT REVENUE GROWTH
DESPITE THE CHANGE IN GUIDANCE,
THE MIDPOINT OF THE GUIDANCE IS
STILL ABOVE THE PRIOR YEAR SO
WE'RE GOING TO GROW.
BUT WE DID ADJUST TO REFLECT THE
NECESSARY CHANGE IN FUEL AND
CURRENCY
I THINK THERE'S CONSTERNATION AS
THERE HAS BEEN FOR SOME TIME
BECAUSE WE HAVE CONSISTENTLY
BEAT FOR THE QUARTER AND THEN
HAD DROPS ON THE CALLS,
SOMETIMES OVERALL MARKET DROPS
I THINK PART OF IT IS JUST A
FEAR AMONGST SOME PEOPLE THAT
THIS IS A CYCLICAL INDUSTRY.
THEY SEE ADDITIONAL CAPACITY
COMING ON AND THEY'RE
ANTICIPATING THAT CYCLE TO TURN
BECAUSE WE HAVE SUCH A GOOD RUN.
BUT WE FEEL THAT -- IN FACT WE
KNOW AND WE PLAN FOR CONTINUING
EARNINGS GROWTH, SUSTAINED
EARNINGS GROWTH IN THE YEARS TO
COME, DOUBLE DIGIT, AND ELEVATED
RETURN ON INVESTMENT CAPITAL
WHICH IS ALREADY DOUBLE DIGIT.
>> BUT HAVE BOOKINGS BEEN A BIT
SOFTER THAN YOU'D HOPED SO FAR
THIS QUARTER
WAS THAT ANOTHER FACTOR?
>> NO, WE SEE NO WEAKNESS.
WE HAVE CAPACITY INCREASE,
BOOKINGS HAVE BEEN STRONG.
IN FACT WE HAVE LESS VOLUME TO
BOOK NOW THAN WE DID LAST YEAR
AND THAT'S WITH CAPACITY
INC
INCREASE
SO WE'RE AHEAD ON BOOKINGS
WE'RE DOING VERY WELL, IT'S JUST
THIS CONSTERNATION AROUND
LOOKING FOR A PARTICULAR YIELD
NUMBER AND THIS FEAR, I BELIEVE,
THAT THE BUSINESS IS CYCLICAL
AND NOT SEEING A YIELD NUMBER IN
THE FACE OF THE CAPACITY
INCREASE REINFORCES SOME OF THE
PERCEPTIONS THAT SOME PEOPLE
HAVE
BUT THE REALITY IS WE'RE GOING
TO DELIVER AND WE BELIEVE WHEN
WE DELIVER, THE VALUE WILL
ACTUALLY BE SHOWN TO THE
SHAREHOLDERS
>> SOME OF THE ANALYSTS ARE
WARNING ABOUT YOUR ABILITY TO
PRICE ON PRICES IN EUROPE
SPECIFICALLY AND CITING THAT FOR
THE UNDERPERFORMANCE OF YOUR
STOCK VERSUS SOME OF YOUR
COMPETITORS.
WHAT'S ACTUALLY HAPPENING IN
EUROPE
>> AGAIN, WE'VE GOT DOUBLE-DIGIT
CAPACITY INCREASE IN EUROPE.
EUROPE IS UNEVEN AS AN
ENVIRONMENT, RIGHT NOW, AS YOU
KNOW
BUT OVERALL WE'RE GOING TO GROW
EARNINGS IN OUR EUROPEAN
FRANCHISE ACROSS OUR BRANDS IN
EUROPE
WE'RE GOING TO GROW EARNINGS
THIS YEAR DESPITE THE UNEVENNESS
AND WHAT HAVE YOU.
AND WE HAVE A SIGNIFICANT
CAPACITY INCREASE.
SO THE YIELD, WHILE ULTIMATELY
WE EXPECT IT TO BE FLATTISH YEAR
TO YEAR, WE'RE GOING TO BE
GROWING EARNINGS
IN THE END, IT'S EARNINGS AND
RETURN ON INVESTMENTCAPITAL
THAT CREATE THE VALUE FOR THE
BUSINESS
AND WE'RE EXCITED.
WE'VE GOT COSTA, ESMERELDA
COMING IN.
CARNIVAL, PANORAMA IS COMING
LATER AND SKY PRINCESS
CARNIVAL MARDI GRAS, WHICH ISN'T
GOING TO BE INTRODUCED UNTIL
2020 HAS 65,000 GUESTS ALREADY
PREREGISTERED.
IT'S THE NEW SHIP THAT WILL HAVE
THE ROLLER COASTER ON IT
IT'S A LOT OF FUN, WE'RE DOING
WELL.
>> ARNOLD, VIKING CRUISES HAD
SOME TROUBLE THIS PAST WEEK,
INCLUDING AN EVACUATION.
WHEN YOU SEE ISSUES LIKE THAT,
DOES IT DRIVE CUSTOMERS TO
CARNIVAL OR IN GENERAL AWAY FROM
CRUISE SHIPS ALTOGETHER?
>> FIRST OF ALL, I'M NOT
FAMILIAR WITH THE SITUATION
THERE.
OBVIOUSLY I DON'T HAVE ANY
AFFILIATION WITH VIKING.
I'M JUST GLAD EVERYBODY -- THERE
WAS NO SERIOUS INJURIES OR
ANYTHING AND EVERYBODY SEEMS TO
BE SAFE AND THAT'S THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING.
BUT THINGS LIKE THAT FOR PEOPLE
WHO HAVEN'T CRUISED, IF IT STAYS
IN THE NEWS FOR A WHILE, IT CAN
BE A DETRIMENT FOR SOMEONE WHO
HADN'T CRUISED YET
FOR PEOPLE WHO CRUISE A LOT, I
THINK THEY REALIZE WHAT A SAFE
VACATION EXPERIENCE IT IS AND
WHAT A SAFE AND SECURE PROSPECT
IT IS TO BE ON A CRUISE SHIP.
>> ARNOLD, STATE OF THE CONSUMER
2019 VERSUS 2018
IS IT OUTLOOK SLOWER
>> YOU KNOW, WE'RE A GLOBAL
BUSINESS AND IT CHANGES EVERY
YEAR AROUND THE WORLD.
BUT THE BOTTOM LINE IS I WOULD
SAY THINGS ARE POSITIVE FOR US
WITH CONSUMERS
OUR ONBOARD REVENUES, WHICH
WOULD BE ONE INDICATOR OF THAT,
OUR ONBOARD REVENUES ARE UP
NICELY IN THE FIRST QUARTER.
WE'RE EXPECTING TO SEE CONTINUED
STRENGTH IN THAT THROUGH THE
REST OF THE YEAR ACROSS THE
BOARD, WHETHER IT'S IN EUROPE OR
IN CHINA OR HERE IN THE U.S.
SO RIGHT NOW WE STILL SEE THINGS
POSITIVE
WE'RE A LITTLE RECESSION
RESISTANT, SO EVEN IF RECESSION
HITS, WE'RE SUCH A MUCH BETTER
VALUE THAN THE LAND-BASED
VACATION THAT WE'RE STILL A GOOD
PLACE TO GO FOR PEOPLE WHO ARE
LOOKING FOR A GREAT TIME, A
GREAT EXPERIENCE AND WONDERFUL
MEMORIES.
>> ARNOLD, I DON'T GET IT.
I'M HAVING A LITTLE DEJA VU
BECAUSE YOU JOINED US AT THE END
OF DECEMBER.
THE STOCK TOOK A BIG DIP AND YOU
CAME ON SAYING THE BUSINESS IS
GREAT, EVERYTHING IS FINE, WALL
STREET IS OVERREACTING
IT LOOKS LIKE THE STOCK HAS
FALLEN ON THE DAY YOU REPORTED
THE LAST FIVE QUARTERS
WHERE'S THE DISCONNECT COMING
FROM BETWEEN WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
AND HOW WALL STREET IS REACTING?
>> I BELIEVE -- I WISH I KNEW
FOR CERTAIN, BUT I BELIEVE THE
BIG DISCONNECT IS THERE IS A
LATENT FEAR THAT THE CYCLE WILL
TURN
THAT WE'VE BEEN ON A NICE, LONG
RUN AND THE CYCLE WILL TURN.
THEY BELIEVE THE BUSINESS IS
CYCLICAL
EACH QUARTER IT'S A DIFFERENT
THING THAT THEY POINT TO TO
CAUSE THEM CONSTERNATION AS WE
CONTINUE TO GROW OUR EARNINGS
AND CONTINUE TO BEAT THE
GUIDANCE
AND I THINK IT'S JUST THIS
LATENT CONCERN
THIS PARTICULAR TIME WE DID
LOWER GUIDANCE BECAUSE OF FUEL
AND CURRENCY, ALTHOUGH THE
GUIDANCE IS STILL FOR AN
IMPROVED EARNINGS PICTURE VERSUS
THE PRIOR YEAR
AND WE HAVE A LOW YIELD
FORECAST, WHICH AGAIN WE'VE GOT
NINE BRANDS.
THAT'S A LONG STORY I WON'T
BOTHER GOING INTO IT
BUT THIS WEIGHTED AVERAGE YIELD
THING.
SO THEY POINT TO THOSE AND IT
MAKES THEM NERVOUS, OBVIOUSLY.
BUT I THINK AS LONG AS WE
PERFORM ULTIMATELY FOR THOSE
SHAREHOLDERS THAT ARE LONG-TERM
INVESTORS, THEY'RE GOING TO BE
HANDSOMELY REWARDED AND THE
OTHERS WILL COME IN AS THEY'RE
CONVINCED THAT WHAT WE'RE SAYING
IS TRUE, WHICH IS WE WILL HAVE
SUSTAINED EARNINGS GROWTH AND
RETURN ON INVESTMENT CAPITAL.
>> ARNOLD, THANK YOU VERY MUCH
ARNOLD DONALD, CEO OF CARNIVAL.
>> YOU'RE NOT ASKING ABOUT THE
TIME CHANGE?
>> YOU REALLY SHUT IT DOWN
EARLIER.
I THOUGHT IT WAS TIME TO MOVE
ON
IT'S ALSO DIFFERENT.
THEY'RE CROSSING TIME ZONES THAN
HAVING DAYLIGHT SAVINGS, SO IT
WOULDN'T HAVE QUITE BEEN THE
RIGHT QUESTION.
>>> WE HAVE 20 MINUTES LEFT OF
TRADE.
WE ARE HIGHER BY 0.3% OR SO BUT
WE HAVE LOST STEAM THROUGHOUT
THE SESSION.
MOST OF THE SECTORS ARE
POSITIVE
I THINK ONE JUST DIPPED INTO THE
RED OF LATE.
SHARES OF BED, BATH AND BEYOND
SOARING TODAY.
WHY ACTIVIST INVESTORS ARE
CALLING FOR ITS ENTIRE BOARD TO
BE REPLACED.
THAT'S COMING UP.
>>> PLUS HOUSING STARTS
STUMBLING TODAY.
AFTER THE BELL WE'LL GET ANOTHER
READ ON HOUSING.
EARNINGS FROM KB HOME COMING
YOUR WAY
"CLOSING BELL" WILL BE RIGHT
BACK
Okay,
paint a picture for me.
Uh, well,
this will be the kitchen.
And we'd like to put
a fire pit out there,
and a dock with a boat, maybe.
Why haven't you
started building?
Well,
Tyler's off to college...
and Mom's getting older...
and eventually we
would like to retire.
Yeah, it's a lot.
But TD Ameritrade can help
you build a plan for today
and tomorrow.
Great.
Can you help us pour
the foundation too?
I think you want a house
near the lake, not in it.
Come with a goal.
Leave with a plan.
TD Ameritrade.
♪♪
I wanna keep doing what I love,
that's the retirement plan.
With my annuity,
I know there is a guarantee.
It's for my family,
its for my self,
its for my future.
Annuities can provide
protected income for life.
Learn more at
Retire Your Risk dot org.
What do advisors look for
in an ETF?
Don't just track an index,
help me meet a client's need.
Is the fund built to sell
or built to last?
ETFs are only part
of a portfolio.
So make it easy to explain.
Give me a quality fund
that helps me get clients closer
to their goals.
FlexShares ETFs are designed
and managed
around investor objectives.
So you can advise
with confidence.
Before investing, consider the
fund's investment objectives,
risks, charges and expenses.
Go to flexshares.com
for a prospectus
containing this information.
Read it carefully.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "THE CLOSING
BELL."
WE HAVE 17 MINUTES LEFT TO
TRADE.
A COUPLE OF INDIVIDUAL MARKET
MOVERS FOR YOU
BED, BATH AND BEYOND SOARING ON
THE REPORT THAT ACTIVIST
INVESTORS WANT TO REPLACE THE
COMPANY'S ENTIRE 12-PERSON
BOARD.
THE INVESTORS WHO HAVE A 5%
STAKE IN THE COMPANY CITED THE
RETAILER'S FAILURE TO ADAPTING
TO CONSUMERS SHOPPING ONLINE
BED, BATH AND BEYOND ISSUED A
STATEMENT SAYING IT REACHED OUT
TO THE ACTIVIST INVESTORS,
INCLUDING LEGION PARTNERS ASSET
MANAGEMENT FOR IDEAS AND
SUGGESTIONS ON IMPROVING ITS
BUSINESS BUT DIDN'T RECEIVE ANY
FEEDBACK FROM THEM WRITING,
UNFORTUNATELY, WHILE OUR
DIRECTORS AND MANAGEMENT WERE
SEEKING TO ENGAGE IN GOOD FAITH,
IT APPEARS THAT THE LEGION AND
MACELLUM REPRESENTATIVES WERE
MERELY SEEKING INFORMATION TO
SUPPORT THEIR OWN ATTACK
SHARES TRADING SHARPLY HIGHER ON
THIS NEWS, SOME 20%.
IT WAS A LITTLE BIT MORE THAN
THAT EARLIER ON.
THE GENERAL TAKE IS THEY THINK
THERE'S A LOT OF LOW-HANGING
FRUIT, WHETHER IT'S CUTTING
COSTS OR MANAGEMENT.
BUT THE MARKET LIKES IT.
>> WE WERE TALKING EARLIER WITH
MIKE SANTOLI ABOUT RETAIL THIS
YEAR FACING SORT OF A MOMENT OF
RECKONING.
IF YOU HAVEN'T FIXED IT IN THIS
VERY HEALTHY CONSUMER
ENVIRONMENT THAT WE'VE HAD IN
THE LAST YEAR, SOMETHING HAS GOT
TO GIVE, WHETHER IT'S GAP
SPLITTING UP ITS BUSINESSES OR
AN ACTIVIST COMING OVER AND
PUTTING A LOT OF PRESSURE TO
REVAMP A BOARD AND A CEO
THESE ARE SOME OF THE
UNDERPERFORMERS.
>> RIGHT
BUT BIG, BIG MOVE IN THE SHARE
PRICE BECAUSE PEOPLE FEEL IT'S
LOW-HANGING FRUIT.
THERE'S ONLY A 5% STAKE HERE
BUT PEOPLE THINK THERE'S EASY
WORK TO BE DONE.
>>> I'M WATCHING ON A CONSUMER
NOTE, McCORMICK BEATING ON
EARNINGS, MEETING ON REVENUE
STRONG PERFORMANCE HELPED OFFSET
THE LIGHTER CONSUMER BUSINESS
SALES.
SHARES TRADING UP A LITTLE LESS
THAN 1% TODAY.
FRANK'S HOT SAUCE HAS BEEN A BIG
PART OF THE STORY HERE
IT HAS BEEN OUTGROWING THE REST
OF THE FOOD PEERS.
THE VALUATION HAS REFLECTED
THAT
IT'S TRADING ABOUT 26 TIMES
FISCAL YEAR '20 EARNINGS
MEDIAN FOOD COMPANY IS JUST
UNDER 20 SO A LOT OF THE
STRENGTH IN McCORMICK AND THE
OUTPERFORMANCE LIKE WE SAW TODAY
HAS BEEN IN THE STOCK.
IT'S BEEN AN AMAZING HIGH FLIER.
A JIM CRAMER FAVORITE AS WELL.
>> FRANK'S HOT SAUCE, I HAVEN'T
TRIED IT YET.
>> CHILULA AND FRANK'S ARE LIKE
STAPLES.
TRY FRANK'S, YOU'LL LIKE IT.
>>> UNDER 15 MINUTES HERE BEFORE
THE CLOSING BELL
WE'VE GOT A 58-POINT RALLY HERE
IN THE DOW, SO THINGS HAVE
COOLED OFF FROM THE TRIPLE-DIGIT
GAIN WE SAW EARLIER.
IT WAS AS HIGH AS 279 POINTS
EARLIER.
BUT WITHIN THE S&P, MOST OF THE
GROUPS ARE STILL HIGHER AT THIS
HOUR, LED MY ENERGY.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, A TOP
STRATEGIST TELLS US THE TWO
HOURS OF THE MARKET THAT COULD
SEE BIG SLOWDOWNS IN THE QUARTER
AHEAD.
WE'RE BACK IN A COUPLE OF.
Woo-hoo.
We've done it! Hah!
Weich and us.
Well I'll be rich,
you'll be famous...
at least amongst
your digging friends.
Here's a thought,
ever consider investing?
E*TRADE has easy to use tools
that help you get started.
You like playing with tools
don't you?
'Course you do.
♪
Don't get mad.
Hi I'm Joan Lunden.
Start investing with E*TRADE.
Today's senior living
communities have never
been better,
with amazing amenities like
movie theaters, exercise rooms
and swimming pools, public
cafes, bars and bistros
even pet care services.
and there's never been
an easier way to get great
advice.
A Place for Mom is a
free service
that pairs you with a local
advisor
to help you sort through
your options
and find a perfect place.
A Place for Mom.
You know your family
We know senior living.
Together we'll make the right
choice.
>>> WELCOME BACK
11 MINUTES LEFT OF TRADE
WE ARE HIGHER BY A THIRD OF 1%
JOINING OUR "CLOSING BELL"
EXCHANGE, LIZ YOUNG AND CNBC'S
RICK SANTELLI.
RICK, THE YIELDS HAVE BEEN IN
SUCH FOCUS OF LATE
TALK US THROUGH THE MOVES TODAY
AND THE AUCTIONS WE'VE HAD
>> YOU KNOW, I WAS VERY
IMPRESSED WITH THE SHORT-END
AUCTION 2-YEAR NOTE YIELDS BUT
IT SHOULDN'T BE SHOCKING
INVESTORS, WHY WOULD THEY TAKE
ALL THE CURVE RISK
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE THE
SHORTEST MATURITY OF THIS $113
BILLION IN SUPPLY MAY BE THE
BEST
TOMORROW WE HAVE 5s FOLLOWED BY
7s
TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTION
SPECIFICALLY, THERE'S SOMETHING
DIFFERENT TODAY ABOUT
TREASURIES
THE EQUITY MARKETS AND INVESTORS
SHOULD GET A LITTLE NERVOUS WHEN
YOU HAVE THAT FREEFALL IN RATES
AND I UNDERSTAND IT COORDINATED
VERY MUCH WITH THE FED,
ESPECIALLY THE 19th WHEN THEY
HAD NO ACTION.
WE WERE AT 2.61 THAT MORNING
AFTER THE FED'S TWO-DAY MEETING,
OBVIOUSLY WE'RE IN THE 2.40s
I THINK IT'S WHETHER IT'S GUN'S
HOT, WHETHER IT HAS KINETIC
ENERGY, WHETHER IT'S CONSTANTLY
MOVING DOWN.
TODAY WE GRABBED
WE WERE UP IN YIELDS EARLY AND
STOCKS AND THE FIXED INCOME
MARKETS TODAY HAVE SHADOW BOXED
ALL SESSION, WILF.
I THINK THAT'S A GOOD THING.
I'M NOT SAYING THIS IS THE
BOTTOM, BUT IT IS THE BOTTOMING
PROCESS AND WE'LL HAVE TO
MONITOR, BUT I THINK THE EQUITY
MARKETS CAN BUILD IF TREASURIES
AT THE VERY LEAST CAN MAINTAIN
AND MOVE A BIT SIDEWAYS.
>> LIZ, WHICH ALSO BRINGS US TO
THE OTHER HOT DISCUSSION POINT
AS OF NOW IN THE BOND MARKET,
THEY'RE PRICING IN A MORE THAN
50% CHANCE THAT THE FEDERAL
RESERVE CUTS INTEREST RATES IN
SEPTEMBER, A MORE THAN 75%
CHANCE THAT THEY DO IT BY NEXT
JANUARY.
WHAT ARE THE IMPLICATIONS FOR
STOCKS OF THAT
>> WELL, FIRST, I THINK THE
MARKET IS A LITTLE AHEAD OF
ITSELF AND WE SEE A POSSIBILITY
FOR A RATE HIKE STILL LATER THIS
YEAR
I MEAN THE FED REALLY PIVOTED
SINCE LAST YEAR UP UNTIL THIS
YEAR
THEY CAN PIVOT AGAIN
IF DATA STAYS STRONG AND THE
U.S. CONSUMER STAYS STRONG, WE
STILL SEE A CHANCE FOR THEM TO
COME BACK TO THE TABLE
THE IMPLICATIONS TO STOCKS IF
THEY CUT LATER THIS YEAR, IF THE
MARKET IS NOT EXPECTING THAT,
THEY'LL THINK THE FED KNOWS
SOMETHING WE DON'T AND THAT'S A
NEGATIVE SIGN.
>> HOW DOES THAT MEAN THAT
YOU'RE POSITIONED RELATIVE TO
THE MARKET IF YOU THINK WE COULD
STILL GET A HIKE AND PEOPLE ARE
MOVING THE OTHER DIRECTION
>> IF YOU LOOK AT IT FROM A BOND
PERSPECTIVE, WITH YIELDS AS LOW
AS THEY ARE, WE THINK THE MARKET
MAY HAVE GOTTEN A LITTLE AHEAD
OF ITSELF.
SO IT'S NOT NECESSARILY TIME TO
CHASE THE CURVE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO TAKE A TON
MORE DURATION RISK WHICH SOUNDS
LIKE THE CONSENSUS TODAY
BUT IN THE STOCK SIDE OF IT, NOT
THAT YOU WANT TO BE OVERWEIGHT
RISK ASSETS BUT THE FACT WE
COULD SEE THEM COME BACK TO THE
TABLE IN THIS PAUSE TABLE, IT'S
GOING TO BE SUPPORTIVE OF RISK
ASSETS
>> DO YOU THINK THE FED WILL
CONTINUE TO BE A PRIMARY DRIVER
FOR RISK SENTIMENT AND STOCKS
FOR THE REST OF THE YEAR AS IT
HAS BEEN FROM THE BEGINNING PART
OF THE YEAR?
>> THEY HAVE BEEN A PRIMARY
DRIVER TO POSITIVE RISK
SENTIMENT IN THE BEGINNING PART
OF THE YEAR.
THE SECOND QUARTER WILL BE
REALLY TOUGH FOR EVERYBODY
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE EARNINGS
COME IN AND RIGHT NOW EARNINGS
ARE EXPECTED TO BE NEGATIVE
3.6%
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE GDP GROWTH
THAT COMES IN A LOT LOWER THAN
THE FOURTH QUARTER SO I THINK
THE MARKET WILL HAVE TO DIGEST
THAT
I DON'T KNOW THAT THE FED CAN
DRIVE THAT MUCH MORE POSITIVITY
THROUGH Q2.
>> RICK, BACK TO THE YIELD
CURVES THIS WEEK
CAN WE REDUCE OUR FOCUS THAT HAS
BEEN SO HIGH OF LATE ON
INTERNATIONAL YIELD?
THE CURVE HAS BEEN MOVING A
LITTLE BIT MORE ON ITS OWN THIS
WEEK, HAS IT NOT
>> A LITTLE BIT.
I THINK WE'LL PAY A WHOLE LOT
MORE ATTENTION TO OVERSEAS
INVESTORS' BEHAVIOR IN LIEU OF
THE FACT THAT THEIR CENTRAL
BANKS MISSED A COUPLE OF
OPPORTUNITIES.
EVEN IF YOU DON'T AGREE WITH
THAT, NOBODY IS GOING TO
DISAGREE THAT NOW IS NOT THE
TIME FOR MARIO DRAGHI TO BE
STEPPING OUT OR MR. CARNEY
SO I THINK THE ANSWER IS THERE'S
GOING TO BE ONGOING PRESSURES.
ONE THING LIZ SAID I ABSOLUTELY
AGREE ON, LISTEN, IF YOU'RE
LOOKING DOWN THE ROAD IN FED
FUND FUTURES, I HARKEN BACK
FOUR, FIVE, SIX MONTHS AGO WHEN
ALL THE TIGHTENING'S WERE BUILT
IN
THE PROBLEM WITH FED FUND
FUTURES AS A BAROMETER IS THAT
IT REALLY ONLY WORKS AS A GOOD
PERCENTAGE, A GOOD CALL FOR THE
NEXT MEETING WHEN YOU'RE THREE
OR FOUR WEEKS FROM THE NEXT
MEETING AND ONLY THE CONTRACT
THAT COVERS THE MEETING.
JUST THINK, IT'S NOT MUCH
DIFFERENT THAN THE STOCK MARKET.
IT LOOKED A LOT BETTER IN AUGUST
THAN IT DID IN OCTOBER AND
NOVEMBER
I WOULD THINK THE SAME COULD BE
SAID FOR FED FUND FUTURES.
IN THE END IT'S A ONE MONTH SORT
OF BILL KCONTRACT
AND WHAT IT SAYS WAY DOWN THE
ROAD DOESN'T FORETELL THE FUTURE
LIKE THE NEAREST CONTRACT MONTH.
>> THE OTHER THING I WOULD POINT
OUT IS THAT OIL PRICES ARE
JUMPING 2%
WTI JUST CROSSING BACK ABOVE $60
A BARREL
DOES THAT INFLUENCE YOUR SECTOR?
>> IT'S A POSITIVE SIGNAL.
IF YOU SEE DEMAND COME BACK INTO
COMMODITIES, IT'S ANOTHER SIGNAL
THAT DEMAND IS HEALTHY IN THE
ECONOMY, WHICH IS GOING TO MAYBE
SURPRISE US ON THE UPSIDE
THROUGHOUT THE SECOND HALF.
>> LIZ, THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> THANK YOU.
>> ICK, AS ALWAYS, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
>>> UP NEXT, WE'LL BE BACK WITH
THE CLOSING COUNTDOWN.
JUST FIVE MINUTES LEFT TO TRADE.
>>> AND ON THE HEELS OF WEAKER
HOUSING DATA THIS MORNING, WE'LL
GET EARNINGS RESULTS FROM KB
HOME AFTER THE BELL.
IT'S UP AROUND 25% SO FAR THIS
YEAR
'LBEIG BK.
Does your Wealth Manager
measure up?
A CFA Charterholder does.
You've worked hard
to grow your wealth.
Make sure you're working
with a Wealth Manager
who can grow with you.
CFA Charterholders have
the investment expertise
to unlock opportunities other
advisors might not see.
Learn what a CFA Charterholdr
can do for you
at therightquestion.org
I consulted with your
grandmother's doctor.
We can do the
screening at her house.
Hi.
This is the man that's going
to check your eyes grandma.
Cognizant AI solutions
are helping healthcare companies
advance diagnostics
and prevent blindness
in patients with diabetes.
Everything looks good.
You have beautiful eyes.
♪♪
So, recently my son's band was
signed by a record label.
A record deal?
Unbelievable.
Whenever we're about to get
on a stage for a huge audience,
I always give my dad, like,
a FaceTime kinda moment.
You see the crowd,
you see the emotion.
You know, he has that experience
for the first time with me,
and that's really
important to me.
I created a rockstar.
(both laughing)
(announcer)
The best network is even better
when you share it.
Buy the latest iPhone for you,
and get iPhone 10R on us
for someone else.
And get Apple Music on us, too.
Only on Verizon.
♪♪
You should be mad they gave this
guy a promotion.
You should be mad at
forced camaraderie.
And you should be mad at tech
that makes things worse.
But you're not mad,
because you have E*TRADE,
who's tech makes life easier
by automatically adding
technical patterns on charts
and helping you understand what
they mean.
Don't get mad.
Get E*TRADE's simplified
technical analysis.
>>> SHARES OF APPLE NEAR SESSION
LOWS FOLLOWING A PATENT RULING
INVOLVING QUALCOMM, HELPING THE
DOW LOSE SOME STEAM TODAY.
JOSH LIPTON WITH MORE IN SAN
FRANCISCO.
WHAT'S THE STORY HERE, JOSH.
>> SARA, WE WANT TO CALL YOUR
ATTENTION TO APPLE WHICH IS NEAR
THE LOWS OF THE SESSION.
QUALCOMM IN THE GREEN HERE
A TRADE JUDGE, A JUDGE WITH THE
ITC, HAS MADE AN INITIAL RULING
SAYING APPLE DID INFRINGE ONE
QUALCOMM PATENT.
IT SOUNDS LIKE THIS JUDGE WILL
RECOMMEND A LIMITED IMPORT BAN
ON SOME iPHONE MODELS.
THAT'S NOT THE END OF THE STORY.
THE FULL ITC COMMISSION HAS TO
REVIEW THIS DECISION
REMEMBER, THIS IS JUST ONE OF
TWO CASES QUALCOMM BROUGHT TO
THE ITC.
THE COMMISSION IS EXPECTED TO
RELEASE ITS FINAL DECISION ON
THE OTHER CASE LATER TODAY
IN THAT ONE LATE LAST YEAR, THE
ITC JUDGE ALSO SAID APPLE HAD
INFRINGED A QUALCOMM PATENT BUT
THAT JUDGE DID NOT RECOMMEND A
INJUNCTION SO WE'RE WAITING TO
SEE WHAT THE FULL ITC COMMISSION
HAS TO SAY ABOUT THAT.
BIGGER PICTURE, THESE TWO HAVE
BEEN BATTLING FOR TWO YEARS.
QUALCOMM GOING AFTER APPLE FOR
PATENT INFRINGEMENT.
SARA, BACK TO YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, JOSH, THANK YOU.
>>> WILFRED, OVER TO YOU ON THE
FLOOR.
>> LET'S START WITH THE S&P 500.
IT WAS A PICTURE LOSING IMPETUS
THROUGHOUT THE SESSION BUT A
NICE TICK-UP FOR THE FINAL HOUR
OF TRADES LEAVES US WITH THE
FOUR INDICES UP A LITTLE MORE
THAN HALF A PERCENT.
THE RUSSELL IS UP NEARLY A FULL
PERCENT.
THE S&P UP 0.7%.
I'M GOING TO GET TO BOB PISANI
AND THE SECTORS CHART.
EVEN THOUGH WE'RE OFF THE HIGHS
OF THE DAY, ALL THE SECTORS IN
POSITIVE TERRITORY.
>> AT LEAST THE YIELDS WERE NOT
DOWN AGAIN
BANKS WERE UP TODAY.
THAT'S POSITIVE.
ENERGY, LOOK, $60 OIL HERE,
THAT'S ESSENTIALLY THE HIGHS FOR
THE YEAR
SO ENERGY STOCKS DID WELL.
WE GOT THAT LOUSY HOUSING NUMBER
EARLY ON TODAY FOR FEBRUARY AND
ALL THE HOME BUILDING STOCKS,
YOU SEE NICE MOVES UP 2% AND 3%.
THIS IS OTHER THAN UTILITIES THE
BEST-PERFORMING OUT THERE.
>> THERE GOES THE BELL
THAT NICE LITTLE RUN-UP LEAVES
US EXACTLY A PERCENT HIGHER ON
THE RUSSELL, WHICH IS THE
OUTPERFORMER TODAY
DOW AND S&P UP MORE THAN HALF OF
1%, SO A DECENT SESSION.
THAT DOES IT FOR THE FIRST HALF
OF "CLOSING BELL."
SARA, BACK TO YOU.
>>> WELCOME TO "CLOSING BELL."
I'M SARA EISEN
WILFRED FROST REJOINING ME IN
JUST A MOMENT AS WELL AS MIKE
SANTOLI AS ALWAYS.
TAKE A LOOK AT HOW WE'RE
FINISHING UP THE DAY ON WALL
STREET
THE DOW CLOSING UP ABOUT HALF A
PERCENT, SORT OF IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE RANGE OF WHERE IT'S BEEN
ALL DAY.
GOT AS HIGH AS 279, AS LOW AS UP
IT GAINED 140 POINTS
DIDN'T HELP THAT APPLE TURNED
LOWER ON THAT QUALCOMM NEWS JOSH
JUST REPORTED.
THE S&P 500 GAINING
THREE-QUARTERS OF A PERCENT.
ENERGY AND FINANCIALS IN THE
LEAD
MORE THAN 1% GAINS APIECE.
TECHNOLOGY HAD A COMEBACK DAY,
UP 0.7 OF 1%
AND THE RUSSELL UP A FULL
PERCENT.
HERE ARE THE STORIES ON OUR
RADAR.
TECH STOCKS DID OUTPERFORM THE
DOW BUT COMPANIES BRACING
INVESTORS FOR WHAT COULD BE THE
WORST QUARTER FOR TECH IN MORE
THAN SIX YEARS.
>>> AND WE'LL GET A READ ON
HOUSING WHEN KB HOMES REPORTS IN
JUST A FEW MINUTES.
>>> FIRST JOINING US TO TALK
ABOUT THE MARKET TODAY, TONY
DWYER.
MIKE, A PRETTY STRONG SESSION.
IT WASN'T AS STRONG AS IT LOOKED
EARLIER THIS MORNING, BUT IT
FELT LIKE IT WAS KEY THAT YIELDS
STABILIZED.
>> IT WAS.
IN THE MORNING THAT SORT OF
RELEASED THE MARKET HIGHER
AND I THINK REALLY WE PEAKED ON
THE DAY IN TERMS OF THE STOCK
INDEXES WHEN THOSE YIELDS ALSO
HIT THEIR HIGHS OF THE DAY SO
WE'RE KIND OF TETHERED FOR THE
MOMENT
WE'LL SEE IF THIS CONTINUES FOR
A WHILE.
MORE BROADLY, I THINK THE S&P
500 IS TRYING TO FIGHT THE
BATTLE OF THIS 2800, THIS TRENCH
THAT'S BEEN DRAWN IN THE MARKET.
WE FIRST HIT IT MARCH 1st.
HERE IT IS MARCH 26th AND WE'RE
WITHIN 1% OF IT.
I THINK WE SPENT MOST OF THE
MONTH HERE
SO I DON'T THINK YOU CAN
CONCLUDE ANYTHING PARTICULARLY
DECISIVE ABOUT TODAY, ALTHOUGH
THE BANKS BOUNCING HARD WAS
PROBABLY WELCOME
WE'LL SEE IF THERE'S ANY
FOLLOW-THROUGH AT ALL.
>> TONY, DO YOU THINK THE EQUITY
MARKETS WANT TO SEE THE YIELDS
STABILIZE A BIT, JUST SOME
STABILITY SO THEY CAN FIND
FOOTING AGAIN?
>> GOING BACK TO THE LEAD-IN
STORY ON TECH AND HOW YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE THE WORST EARNINGS
IN SIX YEARS, IT'S BEEN A GOOD
SIX YEARS DURING THAT TIME SO
LET'S PUT THAT IN PERSPECTIVE.
THE MARKET WANTS TO SEE THERE'S
NOT GOING TO BE PART OF A
RECESSION, GIVEN THAT PART OF
THE YIELD CURVE INVERTED LAST
FRIDAY
IT'S LOOKING FOR ANY KIND OF
SIGNS OF GREEN CHUTES FOR
GROWTH.
>> MIKE, GREEN CHUTES FOR
GROWTH, ARE WE SEEING ENOUGH OF
THEM TO HAVE SEEN THE MARKET RUN
UP SO FAR SO FAST THIS YEAR?
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK MOST OF THE
RALLY YOU COULD PROBABLY CHALK
UP TO THE FED PIVOT, THE FACT
THAT THE MARKET WAS SO OVERDONE
ON THE DOWNSIDE.
I DON'T THINK IT'S BEEN RISING
ON THIS ECONOMY IS ACCELERATING
OR ABOUT TO ACCELERATE.
>> THERE'S SO LITTLE IN THE WAY
OF DATA.
>> VERY LITTLE IN THE WAY OF
DATA
IF YOU LOOK AT THE STOCKS
WORKING THE BEST, THEY'RE NOT
NECESSARILY, AT LEAST IN THE
LAST FEW WEEKS, TETHERED TO HOW
STRONG THE ECONOMY IS.
TODAY YOU HAD THIS BACKSLIDING
IN THE CONSUMER CONFIDENCE
INDEX, WHICH I DON'T THINK IT
SAYS THINGS ARE FALLING APART
BUT IT DOESN'T DO ANYTHING TO
DISSUADE PEOPLE WHO FEEL LIKE
WE'RE IN A PROLONGED SOFT PATCH.
>> EVERYBODY IS LOOKING AT THE
YIELD CURVE AND SAYING PART OF
IT INVERTED.
A LOT OF THINGS HAPPEN BEFORE
YOU GO INTO A RECESSION.
CREDIT DELINQUENCIES PICK UP
THAT'S NOT HAPPENING
CREDIT STRESS INDICATORS THAT
MEASURE 105 CREDIT STRESSES AND
SHADOW BANKING AND THE FINANCIAL
MARKETS START TO TICK UP
SIGNIFICANTLY.
THEY'RE AT A CYCLE LOW
HOUSEHOLD DEBT SERVICE RATIOS
PICK UP.
THAT'S AT A CYCLE LOW.
ALL THOSE THINGS THAT TYPICALLY
SHOW UP WHEN A RECESSION IS
IMMINENT AND A LOT OF TIMES WE
CHOOSE TO IGNORE ARE SIMPLY NOT
SHOWING UP
AS LONG AS THE CREDIT MARKETS
ARE OPEN AND THEY'RE OPEN,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE POSITIVE
ECONOMIC ACTIVITY.
>> ARE THERE ANY ORANGE FLAGS
OUT THERE, THOUGH?
>> WELL, THERE REALLY ISN'T.
THERE'S THIS IDEA -- THE YIELD
CURVE IS AN ORANGE FLAG IF IT
STW
INVERTS.
YOU'RE STARTING TO SEE A RATE OF
CHANGE ON SOME OF THE PMIs
IN 2018 YOU HAD THIS GLOBAL
SYNCHRONIZED RECOVERY THAT
EVERYBODY ON THE PLANET WAS
QUOTING AND YOU WERE BEATING
THOSE EXPECTATIONS
TODAY IT'S THE OPPOSITE.
BUT THE KEY METRIC THAT WE WATCH
IS CREDIT.
DO COMPANIES AND INDIVIDUALS
HAVE ACCESS TO CREDIT, AND THE
ANSWER IS ABSOLUTELY YES RIGHT
NOW.
NOW, IT CAN CHANGE QUICKLY, BUT
THERE'S NO SIGNS.
>> SO YOU SAY YOU ARE PERMEABLE.
ARE YOU STILL OUTFRONT IN THAMES
-- TERMS OF YOUR OUTLOOK?
>> WE'RE AT 2950
SARA, IT'S VERY INTERESTING.
IF THE FED IS EASING BECAUSE
ECONOMIC DATA IS SO WEEK AND
WE'RE IN THIS POLITICAL DRAMA
AND EVERYBODY IS JUMPING ON THIS
1995 BANDWAGON, BUT WHEN THE FED
WENT FROM TIGHTENING FEBRUARY
1st OF 1995 TO EASING IN JULY OF
1995, THE MARKET WAS UP 14%.
IT WENT UP WITH MUCH WEAKER
ECONOMIC DATA AND FEAR CORPORATE
PROFITS WOULD BE NEGATIVE.
>> TECH OUTPERFORMING THE
BROADER MARKET AND REMAINS THE
TOP PERFORMING SECTOR FOR THE
YEAR, THE QQQ ETF UP 14% FOR THE
YEAR
MIKE, IT'S SORT OF DANCING TO
ITS OWN TUNE
THE YIELD PICTURE DOESN'T HAVE
TO INFLUENCE IT IN A WAY YOU
MIGHT OF THOUGHT IT WOULD IN THE
PAST.
>> IT SEEMS TO ME THE MARKET IS
SHOWING A PREFERENCE FOR WHERE
IT CAN RELY ON STRONG CASH
FLOWS.
SO MAYBE IT'S JUST THE MUSCLE
MEMORY, BUT THEY'RE GRABBING FOR
BIG CAP TECH
BUT OTHER GROWTH STOCKS AS WELL.
YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT VISA.
A LOT OF OTHER KIND OF SECULAR
GROWTH TYPE NAMES.
SO THAT IS, I THINK, WHAT'S
HAPPENING RIGHT NOW.
TECH IS GETTING BIG AGAIN.
REMEMBER, THEY SPLIT THE SECTORS
LAST YEAR.
IF YOU WERE TO GO BACK AND PUT
FACEBOOK AND ALPHABET BACK IN
THE TECH SECTOR FROM
COMMUNICATION SERVGICES, YOU HAE
A TREMENDOUS COMMITMENT BY THE
MARKET RIGHT NOW BECAUSE RIGHT
NOW THAT'S WHERE THE EARNINGS
CONFIDENCE LIES.
>> BUT THIS WAS A GROUP, TONY,
THAT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE SAFE AND
INSULATED FROM SOME OF THE MACRO
HEADWINDS, RECESSION CALLS,
STRONG DOLLAR.
WHAT DOES IT TELL YOU NOW THE
OUTLOOK IS BEING CLOUDED EVEN
FOR THESE COMPANIES.
>> YOU'RE COMING OFF A PEAK FOR
SEMIS.
DON'T FORGET HOW BIG CRYPTO WILL
BE FOR THE SEMIS AND YOU'RE
HEARING OF DOUBLE ORDERING
WE'RE COMING OFF OF THAT
THE QUESTION IS CAN THE MARKET
CONTINUE TO RALLY IF TECH GOES
INTO A CONSOLIDATION OR WEAKNESS
MODE
AGAIN, I HATE TO DO IT, BUT
1995, SEMIS UNDERPERFORMED
SIGNIFICANTLY IN THE SECOND HALF
OF THAT YEAR, SIGNIFICANTLY.
AND THAT WAS THE GROWTH ARENA.
SO I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT TO
REMEMBER WHAT'S HAPPENING IS
THAT GROWTH IS SLOWING AND
OFFSETTING THAT MOSTLY WE HAVE
HAD 75 BASIS POINT REDUCTION AND
MARKET DRIVEN RATES.
SO THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE
THAT -- I ACTUALLY HEARD
SOMEBODY TALK ABOUT REFINANCING
TODAY.
WHEN'S THE LAST TIME WE'VE
TALKED ABOUT REFINANCING
IT GOES TO CREDIT AVAILABILITY
IF THE PEOPLE ON THIS DESK AND
PEOPLE WATCHING THE SHOW CAN
CALL UP THEIR MORTGAGE COMPANY
AND SAY I'D LIKE TO REFINANCE MY
DEBT AND THEY CAN DO IT, WE'RE
STILL IN A GROWTH TRAJECTORY
THAT'S GOING TO CHANGE
>> WHAT'S YOUR POINT ON SEMIS,
WE NEED TO KEEP AN EYE ON THOSE
AS A LEADING FACTOR?
>> THEY'RE THE REASON FOR
DECLINE IN EARNINGS FOR TECH
HARDWARE AND SEMIS ARE THE TWO
MAIN CULPRITS.
AGAIN, YOU'RE COMING OFF OF PEAK
EARNINGS
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO MAKE OF
APPLE BECAUSE THEY'RE GOING BACK
AND FORTH IN THEIR EARNINGS
ESTIMATES OVER THE LAST THREE
MONTHS
AT THE ENDI OF THE YEAR AND INT
THE FIRST MONTH IT WAS DOWN ON
THE APPLE PREANNOUNCEMENT AND
NOW IT'S BACK UP ON THE
SERVICES
I THINK IT'S JUST A VERY MIXED
PICTURE.
>> SO WHEN PEOPLE ASK YOU
INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY IS THE
BEST PERFORMING SECTOR SO FAR
THIS YEAR, UP 19%, SHOULD WE
STICK WITH IT, WHAT DO YOU SAY
>> ABSOLUTELY.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE -- TO BE OUT OF
AN ECONOMICALLY SENSITIVE
SECTOR, YOU WANT TO BE ABLE TO
SAY THAT CREDIT IS SHOWING
YOU'RE GETTING TOWARD AN
IMMINENT RECESSION
YOU'LL HAVE PERIODS -- HOW MANY
PERIODS HAVE WE HAD THIS CYCLE
WHERE UTILITIES AND CONSUMER
STAPLES HAVE OUTPERFORMED.
PEOPLE HAVE SCREAMED THIS IS A
CHARACTER CHANGE IN THE MARKET
WHEN THESE DEFENSIVE SECTORS
OUTPERFORM ONLY TO REVERSE WHEN?
WHEN INTEREST RATES COME DOWN.
THAT'S WHAT WE'VE HAD OVER THE
COURSE OF THE LAST SIX MONTHS,
MARKET-DRIVEN INTEREST RATES
COME DOWN TO THE POINT YOU'RE
ALMOST AT AN INVERTED YIELD
CURVE.
>>> TECH COMPANIES ARE LOWERING
THEIR EARNINGS GUIDANCE AT A
RECORD RATE.
26 S&P TECH COMPANIES ISSUING
NEGATIVE GUIDANCE AHEAD OF FIRST
QUARTER RESULTS.
FULL STORY ON CNBC.COM
A LOT HAVING TO DO WITH THE
CLOUDY OUTLOOK.
>> WELL, IT'S FUNNY YOU SAY THAT
BECAUSE IT'S SOME OF THE CLOUD
COMPANIES THAT HAVE BEEN
REDUCING THE NUMBERS ALONG WITH
SEMIS.
I THINK IT'S IN THE MARKET ONCE
THE GUIDANCE IS OUT THERE SO
THAT'S ONE OF THOSE THINGS
YOU'RE NOT SURE WHAT TO MAKE OF
IT
IS IT THE BEGINNING OF A
DOWNSLOPE OR AN ADJUSTMENT THE
MARKET HAS MADE TO A SLIGHTLY
LESS INTERESTING EARNINGS GROWTH
FOR AT LEAST A QUARTER OR TWO.
RIGHT NOW I LOOK AT THE SOFTWARE
GROUP, WHICH HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH APPLE
IT IS UP MORE THAN 20% YEAR TO
DATE
SOFTWARE AND SEMIS BOTH UP 20%
YEAR TO DATE
APPLE HAVING THIS NICE RUN
I DON'T THINK THE MARKET IS
SITTING THERE SAYING, OKAY, WE
HAVE TO HUDDLE DOWN BECAUSE TECH
IS NO LONGER AN EARNINGS STORY.
>> TONY?
>> I COULD SEE A PULLBACK.
YOU'RE GETTING CLOSE TO THE
QUARTER WITH EXPECTATION AND
EARNINGS
BUT WHAT I'D URGE EVERYBODY TO
DO, YOU KNOW HOW THE SECOND
DERIVATIVE IS ONLY TALKING ABOUT
WHEN THINGS ARE TURNING OVER
LOOK
WHEN THEY'RE STARTING TO BOUNCE
OFF THE LOW.
THAT'S YOUR TELL THAT YOU'RE
COMING OUT OF THIS GROWTH
SLOWDOWN.
>> IS THAT HAPPENING
WHICH COUNTRIES.
>> IT'S HAPPENING IN CHINA, IT'S
HAPPENING IN THE EUROZONE, IT'S
HAPPENING NEARLY EVERYWHERE.
I TRACK IT AS THE ASIAN FIVE
AND THESE INDICES ARE NEGATIVE
I'M NOT SAYING THEY'RE GOOD.
>> I THINK PEOPLE THOUGHT THAT
AND THEN WE GOT THAT GERMAN
MANUFACTURING NUMBER LAST
FRIDAY.
>> THE ZEW INDEX OF BUSINESS
CONFIDENCE THAT SURPRISED TO THE
UPSIDE.
>> IT'S AN OPTIMISTIC --
>> I AM NOT MAKING THE
OPTIMISTIC CASE.
I AM MAKING THE LESS PESSIMISTIC
CASE
REMEMBER, EVERYBODY WANTS TO
SELL WHEN THINGS ARE GREAT AND
IT'S GETTING LESS GREAT.
LET'S LOOK TO DO THE SAME WHEN
THE SIGNS COME OUT AND IT'S LESS
HORRIFICALLY BAD IN SOME OF
THESE PMIs
THE PERCENTAGE OF PURCHASING
MANAGERS INDEX GLOBALLY THAT ARE
POSITIVE IS BELOW THE LEVEL OF
IT'S TRENDING TO 2011.
THAT'S TYPICALLY NOT WHEN YOU
WANT TO GET NEGATIVE ON GLOBAL
ECONOMIC ACTIVITY.
>> IS IT THE TIME TO START
GETTING AGGRESSIVE WHEN IT'S
LESS BAD NEWS WHEN THE MARKET IS
ONLY 4% OFF ITS ALL-TIME HIGH?
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE AT DEPRESSED
LEVELS.
>> WERE WE AS BAD AS THE GREAT
DEPRESSION IN THE FOURTH
QUARTER?
THERE WAS AN EXCESSIVE DROP IN
THE FOURTH QUARTER
I THINK THE DATA THAT CAME OUT
AND SAID PEOPLE ARE LESS EXPOSED
TO STOCKS SINCE 2016, I DON'T
THINK THEY'RE REALLY BULLISH
YOU'RE NOT A 60% OF NEWS WRITERS
BULLISH, YOU'RE UP OFF THE LOW
BUT CLEARLY THEY'RE NOT CHASING.
PEOPLE ARE FEARFUL OF CHASING.
>> WE WANT TO GET TO THIS NEWS
ALERT ON PATRIOTS OWNER ROBERT
KRAFT.
SUE HERERA WITH THE DETAILS.
SUE.
>>> THE PATRIOTS OWNER ROBERT
KRAFT HAS DECIDED THAT HE IS
GOING TO WAIVE ARRAIGNMENT
HE IS ENTERING A PLEA OF NOT
GUILTY TO CHARGES OF SOLICITING
PROSTITUTION
HE IS ALSO REQUESTING A JURY
TRIAL.
SO HE IS FORMALLY ENTERING A
PLEA OF NOT GUILTY, WAIVING
ARRAIGNMENT AND REQUESTING A
JURY TRIAL
NOW, YOU MAY RECALL JUST A WEEK
OR SO AGO FEDERAL -- FLORIDA
PROSECUTORS HAD OFFERED TO DROP
THE CHARGES AGAINST NOT ONLY MR.
KRAFT BUT OTHER HIGH-PROFILE
PEOPLE IF -- THERE WAS A CATCH
TO THAT.
IF THE MEN AGREED TO ADMIT THAT
THEY WOULD HAVE BEEN FOUND
GUILTY AT TRIAL, THEN THEY WERE
ALSO GOING TO HAVE TO DO
COMMUNITY SERVICE.
THEY REJECTED THAT PARTICULAR
OFFER FROM PROSECUTORS AND NOW
HE HAS ENTERED A PLEA OF NOT
GUILTY TO CHARGES OF SOLICITING
PROSTITUTION
GUYS, BACK TO YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, SUE HERERA, THANK
YOU FOR THE UPDATE ON THAT ONE.
>>> GUYS, I WANT TO GET A FINAL
THOUGHT ON THE MARKETS, TONY
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT THE TECH
OUTLOOK.
LET'S BROADEN IT OUT
OTHER SECTORS THAT LOOK
ATTRACTIVE GOING INTO EARNINGS
SEASON BASED ON
PREANNOUNCEMENTS
>> I THINK THE INTEREST RATE
SENSITIVE SECTORS ARE CONTINUING
TO ACT WELL.
I CAN SEE THE HOME BUILDERS
DOING BETTER ON LOWER RATES AS
YOU GET A LITTLE MORE OPTIMISM
TOWARD SECOND HALF
BUT I WANT TO GO BACK TO THAT
QUESTION WILF BROUGHT UP
THINGS ARE NOT GOOD
INTERNATIONALLY.
MY POINT IS JUST LIKE THE ZEW
INDEX, IF THEY'RE JUST TICKING
UP A LITTLE BIT, THAT'S A LOT
LESS BAD.
>> BUT THERE'S A BIG DIFFERENCE
AS WELL.
VALUATIONS IN EUROPE ARE
UNBELIEVABLY CHEAP
THAT DOESN'T APPLY HERE.
SO A SMALL TICK-UP OR SMALL BIT
OF DATA THAT'S LESS BAD IN
GERMANY, DOES THAT CHANGE THE
OUTLOOK FOR U.S. EQUITIES?
>> I'VE NOT YET FOUND ANYBODY
THAT TRADES THE VALUATION SD
DISCREPANCY BETWEEN THE U.S. FOR
A LONG TIME.
IT COMES DOWN TO GROWTH
EXPECTATIONS
WHEN YOU'VE GOT LOWER INTEREST
RATE AND FAVORABLE MONETARY
POLICY, EMERGING AND HIGHER BETA
DOES BETTER THAN DEVELOPED AND
LOWER BETA.
>> THANKS VERY MUCH, TONY DWYER.
>>> DIGITAL AD COMPANY TRADE
DESK JUST STRUCK A NEW DEAL TO
TARGET ADS IN CHINA.
THE CEO WILL GIVE US DETAILS,
NEXT.
>>> THE STATE OF OKLAHOMA AND
PURDUE PHARMA, THE MAKER OF
OXYCODONE, REACHING A $270
MILLION SETTLEMENT
THE COMPANY HAS MORE COSTLY
LEGAL FIGHTS AHEAD
WE'LL HAVE THE FULL STORY COMING
UP.
>>> YOU CAN REACH OUT TO THE
SHOW ON TWIR, FATTER, FACEBOOK
SEND US AN E-MAIL.
"CLOSING BELL" WILL BE RIGHT
BACK
The day after chemo
might mean a trip back
to the doctor's office
just for a shot.
But why go back there
when you can stay home
with Neulasta Onpro?
Strong chemo can put you at
risk of serious infection.
In a key study Neulasta
reduced the risk of infection
from 17% to 1%,
a 94% decrease.
Neulasta Onpro is designed
to deliver Neulasta
the day after chemo
and is used by most patients
today.
Neulasta is for certain
cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta if you're
allergic to it
or Neupogen (filgrastim).
An incomplete dose could
increase infection risk.
Ruptured spleen,
sometimes fatal as well as
serious lung problems,
allergic reactions,
kidney injuries and capillary
leak syndrome have occurred.
Report abdominal or shoulder
tip pain, trouble breathing
or allergic reactions to
your doctor right away.
In patients with sickle
cell disorders,
serious, sometimes fatal crises
can occur.
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
If you'd rather be home,
ask your doctor about
Neulasta Onpro.
Pay no more than $5 per dose
with copay card.
>>> WELCOME BACK
WE'VE GOT AN EARNINGS ALERT ON
KB HOME.
>> KIND OF A MIXED BAG REPORTING
FIRST QUARTER EARNINGS PER SHARE
OF 31 CENTS.
THAT ON REVENUE OF $811 MILLION
VERSUS ESTIMATES OF $831.8
MILLION.
AVERAGE SELLING OF A KB HOME
DOWN 5% TO $370,900.
THE BIG NUMBER IS THE NEW
ORDERS
THAT'S WHAT EVERYONE WAS
WATCHING BECAUSE OF THE SLOWDOWN
AT THE END OF THE YEAR
KB HOMES' FIRST QUARTER IS
DECEMBER, JANUARY, FEBRUARY, SO
IT WAS WHEN WE SAW MORTGAGE
RATES REALLY PEAK IN NOVEMBER
AND THAT DROPOFF
THE RATES BEGAN COMING DOWN IN
DECEMBER BUT THE END OF THE YEAR
WAS ROUGH FOR THE BUILDERS
NEW ORDERS DOWN 4%
CEO JEFF METZGER SAID ALTHOUGH
THE DECLINE IN NET NEW ORDERS
IMPACTED OUR FIRST QUARTER
HOUSING REVENUES, WE ARE
ENCOURAGED BY IMPROVING MARKET
CONDITIONS WHICH SHOULD ENABLE
US TO GENERATE STRONGER REVENUES
IN THE SECOND HALF
THAT MAY BE POSSIBLE GIVEN MUCH
LOWER RATES BUT SEEING THE PRICE
OF A HOME COME DOWN A LITTLE,
AFFORDABILITY HAS BEEN THE BIG
STORY IN HOUSING
WE DID SEE HOUSING STARTS DROP
OFF IN THE REPORT TODAY FOR
FEBRUARY WITH BUILDERS SEEING
WEAKER DEMAND.
SO AGAIN IT'S KIND OF A BIG
QUESTION MARKUP IN THE AIR FOR
THE SPRING SEASON FOR THE
BUILDERS
WE DID SEE KB HOMES STOCK REALLY
SURGE BUT THAT'S PART OF THE
HOPE TRADE FOR THE BUILDERS.
THAT PEOPLE BUY INTO THEM ON THE
EXPECTATION THAT THE STOCK WILL
INCREASE IF THEY HAVE A GOOD
SEASON
BUT SO FAR WE HAVEN'T REALLY
SEEN THE NEW HOME SALES POP UP
THE WAY WE MIGHT EXPECT.
BACK TO YOU GUYS.
>> DIANA, THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR THAT
MIKE, THE SHARES CLEARLY
REACTING
THE MARGIN WAS PRETTY GOOD
THE OUTLOOK FOR THE YEAR AHEAD
WILL BE WHETHER FALLING RATES
LEADS TO NET ORDERS PICKING BACK
UP AGAIN.
>> IF YOU'RE A HOME BUILDER AND
THE ISSUE THAT HAS TO BE
ADDRESSED IS BRIDGING THIS
AFFORDABILITY GAP, THAT'S NOT
NECESSARILY IDEAL FOR YOUR
BUSINESS
IT MEANS EITHER CUTTING PRICES
OR SOMETHING
OR OF COURSE RATES GOING DOWN
HELPS THAT A LITTLE BIT.
SO IT'S A MIX.
I MEAN THIS STOCK MADE SUCH A
PEAK IN JANUARY OF LAST YEAR,
IT'S BEEN FIGHTING ITS WAY BACK
FROM THE LOWS OFF OF THAT.
IT'S A CONSTRUCTIVE BUT VERY
INCONCLUSIONIVE.
>>> A WINNING STOCK TO TELL YOU
ABOUT, THE TRADE DESK ANNOUNCING
A NEW DEAL TO TARGET ADS IN
CHINA.
THAT STOCK DOWN 5%, BUT UP
ALMOST 240% OVER THE LAST 12
MONTHS
JOINING US NOW IS JEFF GREEN,
CEO AND FOUNDER OF THE TRADE
DESK
WELCOME.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WE DO WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE
NEW DEAL IN CHINA, BUT WE DON'T
TALK ABOUT AD TECH EVERY SINGLE
DAY SO WHAT'S LEADING TO THAT
GROWTH OVER THE LAST YEAR?
>> IT'S BEEN ALMOST 1,000% SINCE
WE LAUNCHED.
ADVERTISERS ARE SAYING THEY WANT
TO PUT THEIR DATA TO WORK AND
REALIZED THAT THE INTERNET IS
WAY BIGGER THAN JUST GOOGLE AND
FACEBOOK
THEY'RE INTERESTED IN MONETIZING
THE REST OF IT, NOT THE LEAST OF
WHICH IS CONNECTED TV AND THE
REST OF THE WORLD, WHICH IS MORE
THAN TWO-THIRDS OF THE
ADVERTISING PIE.
>> SO WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU DO FOR
THEM
>> BASICALLY IF YOU WANT TO BUY
GOOGLE, YOU GO TO GOOGLE
IF YOU WANT TO BUY FACEBOOK, YOU
GO TO FACEBOOK
IF YOU WANT TO BUY THE REST OF
THE ENTRANT, THEY HAND US THEIR
DATA AND INSIGHT AND SAY SHOULD
WE BUY SPOTIFY, "THE NEW YORK
TIMES," MSN OR THIS APP?
WE USE INSIGHTS ON REPORTING TO
HELP THEM WHICH OF THOSE THINGS
TO BUY AND WE MEASURE THE IMPACT
OF EACH OF THEM ON EACH OTHER.
>> AND THESE VARIOUS CONCERNS,
MOST OF IT FOCUSED ON GOOGLE AND
FACEBOOK ABOUT THEIR USE OF USER
DATA AND HOW MUCH ADVERTISERS
HAVE ACCESS TO, WHERE DO YOU SIT
IN THAT PROCESS WITH THESE OTHER
VENUES
>> SO WE'RE VERY DIFFERENT FROM
THOSE TWO COMPANIES IN THE SENSE
THAT WE DON'T TRACT IN
PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE
INFORMATION AND YOU DON'T TELL
ME EVERY TIME YOU HAVE A MEDICAL
PROBLEM OR SHARE WITH ME YOUR
ENTIRE SOCIAL NETWORK.
ALL WE DO IS HELP PEOPLE FIGURE
OUT WHAT PRODUCTS THEY'RE LIKELY
TO BE INTERESTED IN SO IT'S VERY
BENIGN
THAT MAKES US BOTH CONSUMER SAFE
AS WELL AS THE BRANDS TRUST US
THAT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
FOR OUR BUSINESS
OF COURSE WE HAVE TO BE CONSUMER
FRIENDLY, BUT WE ALSO HAVE TO DO
THE RIGHT THING FOR BRANDS
BOTH CONSUMERS AND BRANDS ARE
INTERESTED IN EACH OTHERS'
INTEREST, IF YOU WILL.
>> HOW MUCH DOES ACQUIRING A BIG
CLIENT LIKE PROCTER & GAMBLE IN
ANY GIVEN QUARTER BUOY THE
OVERALL BUSINESS
>> BECAUSE OF THE FACT THAT WE
POWER THE MAJORITY OF THE S&P
500'S PROGRAMATIC TRANSACTIONS,
THERE'S NO ONE COMPANY THAT
MOVES THE NEEDLE IN ANY BIG OR
SMALL WAY.
OF COURSE P & G IS MUCH BIGGER
IN THEIR ADVERTISING SPEND THAN
REALLY ANYBODY ELSE.
BUT WHEN YOU ADD THAT TO THE
WHOLE, IT'S A VERY BIG HEAD.
>> YOU MENTIONED CONNECTED TV.
IT'S AN AREA THAT'S GROWING VERY
FAST
WHAT DID YOU MAKE OF APPLE'S
ANNOUNCEMENT YESTERDAY AND THE
BALANCE BETWEEN THE STREAMING
SERVICES OF WHO HAS ADS AND WHO
HAS JUST SUBSCRIPTIONS
>> YEAH.
SO APPLE'S ANNOUNCEMENT DOESN'T
SURPRISE ME AT ALL
IT'S THE BYPRODUCT OF BASICALLY
OUR ENTIRE INDUSTRY MARCHING
TOWARD A TRILLION DOLLARS.
ADVERTISING WILL BE A TRILLION
DOLLAR INDUSTRY IN LESS THAN TEN
YEARS.
WHETHER YOU'RE AMAZON OR APPLE,
YOU HAVE TO BE LOOKING AT
TRILLION DOLLAR INDUSTRIES AND
GETTING IN ADS IS EASIER THAN
DRILLING FOR OIL
BUT THERE'S A HUGE OPPORTUNITY
IN CONNECTED TV BECAUSE THE
AVERAGE CONSUMER WAS ON NETFLIX,
THEY WERE ON AMAZON, AND NOW THE
SUBSCRIPTION MODELS ARE LESS
APPEALING THAN THE AD-FUNDED
MODELS
SO, FOR INSTANCE, IN OUR Q2 OVER
LAST YEAR WE SAW 21X GROWTH IN
INVENTORY AND THAT'S JUST A
BYPRODUCT OF MORE AND MORE
VIEWERS GOING TO THINGS WHERE
THERE ARE ADS INSTEAD OF PAYING
THE EXPENSIVE PRICE OF CABLE,
WHICH IS AD FUNDED, AND NETFLIX,
AND A BUNCH OF OTHER
SUBSCRIPTIONS THAT DON'T HAVE
ADS.
>> IS THAT WHY YOU'VE BEEN
PREDICTING THAT NETFLIX WILL GO
TO AN AD MODEL
>> I DO THINK THEY WILL GO TO AN
AD MODEL
THEY HAVE SO MUCH AMBITION IN
THE REST OF THE WORLD WHERE IT'S
TOO EXPENSIVE TO PAY $15 A
MONTH.
THEY ENVY THE REACH OF YOUTUBE
IN MARKETS WHERE IT'S JUST
REALLY EXPENSIVE TO HAVE A
SUBSCRIPTION
I THINK EVENTUALLY THEY'LL OFFER
BOTH
THE MAJORITY OF CONSUMERS WOULD
RATHER SEE ADS AND PAY LESS.
>> WE'VE BEEN SO INTERESTED IN
THE BUSINESS WE HAVEN'T GONE ON
TO THE DEAL TODAY.
TELL US ABOUT THAT
SO FAR THERE'S BEEN QUITE A LOT
OF PROTECTIONISM IN CHINA WITH
THE BIG TECH COMPANIES
IT'S JUST NOT LETTING ANYONE
ELSE IN.
>> YEAH, SO WHY TO ALIBABA AND
TENCENT HAVE MORE MARKET SHARE
THAN THEIR EQUIVALENTS HERE?
THE THING THAT IS INTERESTING
ABOUT THE POSITION WE'RE IN,
BECAUSE WE'RE NOT A MEDIA
COMPANY, WE THINK WE'RE ONE OF
THE FEW COMPANIES IN THE WORLD
THAT CAN PARTNER WITH ALL OF
THEM AT THE SAME TIME AND APPLE
AS WELL.
WE PARTNERED WITH THEM IN THE
PAST
IT'S POSSIBLE WE CAN DO THAT
AGAIN.
BUT THE THING THAT'S REALLY
INTERESTING ABOUT ALIBABA AND
T
TENCENT, THEY HAVE HAD A GO IT
ALONE STRATEGY
THEY NEED TO GET MORE OF THEIR
FAIR SHARE OF SPEND RELATIVE TO
WHERE CONSUMERS ARE SPENDING
MONEY THAN THEY HAVE IN THE
PAST
AND THAT MEANS MOSTLY GETTING
ADVERTISING SPEND FROM COMPANIES
THAT ARE NOT BASED IN CHINA.
SO BECAUSE WE PARTNER WITH ALL
THESE COMPANIES ALREADY AND
THEY'RE LOOKING TO PUT THEIR
DATA TO WORK, THEY NEED TO TAKE
IT INTO CHINA WITH A PARTNER
THAT THEY TRUST.
IT'S MUCH HARDER FOR TENCENT TO
SAY GIVE US YOUR DATA AND WE'LL
HELP YOU BUY ADS THAN IT IS FOR
US, WHO THEY ALREADY WORK WITH,
TO SAY, HEY, WE CAN PROTECT IT
AND HELP YOU MAKE DECISIONS
BETWEEN TENCENT, ALIBABA OR
ICHIE OR ANY OF THE OTHERS.
>> HAS THERE BEEN A BIG SLOWDOWN
THERE ALONG WITH WHAT WE'VE SEEN
ECONOMICALLY IN CHINA?
>> I THINK MORE AND MORE IT'S
GOING TO BE DRIVEN BY MARKETING.
IF YOU'RE GOOD AT IT, YOU WILL
WIN MARKET SHARE AND IF YOU'RE
NOT, YOU'RE NOT.
I DO THINK THERE'S SOME
CYCLICALITY TO IT.
BUT IF YOUR NOT ADVERTISING
WELL, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE
DOING WELL
YOU HAVE TO ADVERTISE IN GOOD
MARKETS AND IN BAD MARKETS.
>> JEFF GREEN, THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> MIKE SANTOLI HAS A MYSTERY
CHART FOR US TODAY
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT IT IS OR
WHAT IT MEANS.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHAT I FEAR
>> THAT NEITHER OF US WILL
FIGURE IT OUT.
>> NO, I DON'T MIND ABOUT THAT
MY FEAR IS THAT YOU WILL FIGURE
IT OUT AND I WON'T.
>> WELL, THAT'S PROBABLY LIKELY,
OR ELSE I'LL BE VERY MAD AT MIKE
SANTOLI.
>> WE WILL
YES, I'M GOING TO START THINKING
NOW.
>> BY THE WAY, LAST TIME THAT'S
WHAT HAPPENED.
>> NO.
I DON'T ACCEPT THAT.
I DO NOT ACCEPT THAT
ANYWAY, THIS TIME IS WHAT
MATTERS.
THAT'S COMING AFTER THE BREAK.
>>> SO IS THE FACT THAT PURDUE
PHARMA HAS DECIDED TO PAY THE
LARGEST SETTLEMENT YESTERDAY
THE COMPANY FACES MORE CLAIMS
THAT IT UNDERPAID THE DRUG
ADDICTIVES AS WE'RE BACK IN A
COUPLE OF MINUTES.
>>> TIME FOR A CNBC NEWS UPDATE
WITH SUE HERERA.
>> HELLO, EVERYONE
HERE'S WHAT'S HAPPENING AT THIS
HOUR
ON CAPITOL HILL SENATOR MINORITY
LEADER CHUCK SCHUMER BASHING
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S LATEST FED
PICK, STEPHEN MOORE, SAYING THE
CONSERVATIVE ECONOMIST DOESN'T
HAVE THE RIGHT STUFF TO JOIN THE
FEDERAL RESERVE'S BOARD OF
GOVERNORS.
>> MR. MOORE DOESN'T HAVE THE
BACKGROUND, HE'S A POLITICIAN.
HE'S POLITICAL
HE'S ALWAYS WANTED CUT TAXES,
CUT TAXES, CUT TAXES
HE'S ONE OF THE REASONS WE HAVE
SUCH A BIG DEFICIT RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE OF HIS ADVOCACY.
>>> CHICAGO OFFICIALS CALLING
THE DECISION TO DROP ALL CHARGES
AGAINST ACTOR JUSSIE SMOLLETT AN
OUTRAGE.
THE MAYOR AND CHIEF OF POLICE
HOLDING A BRIEF NEWS CONFERENCE
AFTER THE DECISION.
>> HE DID THIS ALL IN THE NAME
OF SELF-PROMOTION AND HE USED
THE LAWS OF THE HATE CRIME
LEGISLATION THAT ALL OF US
COLLECTIVELY OVER YEARS HAVE PUT
ON THE BOOKS TO STAND UP TO THE
VALUES THAT EMBODY WHAT WE
BELIEVE IN
THIS IS A WHITEWASH OF JUSTICE
>>> YOU ARE UP TO DATE
THAT'S THE NEWS UPDATE THIS
HOUR, WILF, SARA, I'LL SEND IT
BACK DOWNTOWN TO YOU.
>> SUE, THANKS VERY MUCH FOR
THAT.
>>> MIKE IS OVER AT THE
TELESTRATOR WITH TODAY'S MYSTERY
CHART.
WE TEASED THE ASPECT OF IT
YOU'LL HAVE TO GIVE US A CLUE.
>> I WILL GIVE YOU A CLUE.
THIS IS THE PRICE -- JUST
DISREGARD THE M OVER HERE.
THAT'S A STOCK PRICE OF AN ETF,
VERY LARGE, THAT'S DONE VERY
WELL OVER THE LAST FIVE YEARS.
IT IS NOT A SECTOR OF THE
MARKET, BUT IT IS A STYLE OF
INVESTING, A CATEGORY THE STOCKS
OF A CERTAIN FLAVOR.
>> QQQ.
>> IT IS NOT THE QQQ.
>> GROWTH?
>> BOND PROXIES.
>> SARA IS CORRECT
MINIMUM VOLATILITY ETF
STOCKS THAT HAVE -- AS A
PORTFOLIO, LOWER VOLATILITY THAN
THE OVERALL MARKET
IT IS SIMILAR TO THE SPOV BUT
THIS IS A PORTFOLIO OF STOCKS
PUT TOGETHER STRICTLY TO ACHIEVE
LOWER VOLATILITY
YOU SEE HOW MUCH DEMAND THIS HAS
BEEN
IN THEORY THIS SHOULD NOT HAVE
AS GOOD OF RETURNS AS THE
OVERALL MARKET OVER A LONG
PERIOD OF TIME BECAUSE YOU'RE
TAKING LESS RISK
IT'S AT AN ALL-TIME HIGH RIGHT
HERE
HERE'S WHAT'S INTERESTING TO ME.
THIS IS ANOTHER PERIOD WHERE IT
ACCELERATED HIGHER
THIS IS 2016
WE ARE BACK IN THAT 2016 TYPE OF
MARKET
LOW INTEREST RATES, BUT BUYING
THESE BOND PROXY STOCKS.
THIS WAS A PRETTY IMPORTANT
PEAK, IT WAS UP OVER THE COURSE
OF THE PRIOR TWO YEARS 25% IN A
FLATTISH MARKET.
SAME THING RIGHT HERE OVER THESE
TWO YEARS.
SO IT RAISES THE SAME QUESTION
ARE PEOPLE JUST HIDING IN THIS
AREA AND IT'S GOING TO GET
UNWOUND SOMEHOW IF WE GET BETTER
GROWTH.
>> OR PEOPLE HAVE BEEN CALLING
THE DEATH OF THE MULTI-DECADE
BULL MARKET IN BONDS FOREVER AND
EVER AND EVER.
EVERY TIME WE GET A FAKE-OUT
LIKE LAST FALL --
>> YOU DO GET EARNINGS GROWTH
ALONG WITH IT BUT THAT'S WHAT WE
GOT.
>> I THINK I WON.
>> NO, NOBODY WON.
>> I THINK THE SCORE IS 2-0,
SARA
>> WHAT WAS THE LAST TIME?
>> IT WAS AN UNDER ARMOUR CHART.
>> MIKE JUST GAVE YOU THE WIN
AND YOU'VE PASSED IT ON.
>> NOT ONLY DID I WIN BUT I
REMEMBERED.
>> THAT'S FINE
I'LL FIGHT BACK.
WE'VE GOT MANY, MANY HUNDREDS OF
SHORES TO COME
2-0 MEANS NOTHING.
>>> PURDUE PHARMA FACING MORE
THAN 1500 LAWSUITS LINKED TO ITS
PAIN KILLERS
THE COMPANY MADE A MAJOR
SETTLEMENT WITH THE STATE OF
OKLAHOMA TODAY
BUT THE FAMILY THAT OWNS PURDUE
IS FACING FALLOUT IN UNEXPECTED
AREAS.
>>> AMAZON IS GETTING MORE BRICK
AND MORTAR COMPETITION AS
ANOTHER INTERNET RETAILER IS
PLANNING TO OPEN A PHYSICAL
RETAIL STORE
WE'LL SIZE UP THE PROSPECTS FOR
THIS PLAYER COMING UP.
My experience with USAA
has been excellent.
They really appreciate
the military family
and it really shows.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
It was funny because
when we would call
another insurance company,
hey would say
“Oh we can't beat USAA”
We're the Webber family.
We're the Tenney's
We're the Hayles,
and we're USAA members for life.
♪
Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
>>> OPIOID MAKER PURDUE PHARMA
REACHING A $270 MILLION
SETTLEMENT OVER ITS OXYCONTIN
DRUG BUT STILL FACES HUNDREDS
OFOF
OTHER LAWSUITS
ADITI ROY HAS THE STORY.
>> TODAY'S SETTLEMENT COULD BE
JUST THE TIP OF THE ICEBERG FOR
PURDUE PHARMA WHICH FACES OVER A
THOUSAND OTHER CASES
THE MAJORITY OF THE MONEY WILL
GO TOWARDS A NATIONAL ADDICTION
CENTER AT OKLAHOMA STATE
UNIVERSITY.
>> IT IS GOING TO SAVE COUNTLESS
LIVES AND IT'S GOING TO KEEP
FAMILIES TOGETHER.
AND IT'S GOING TO BE THE TIP OF
THE SPEAR IN TERMS OF LEADING
THE NATION OUT OF THE ADDICTION
EPIDEMIC THAT HAS CLAIMED JUST
THIS PAST YEAR 70,000 LIVES.
>> THE AGREEMENT ALSO MEANS TWO
MEMBERS OF THE SACKLER FAMILY
WHICH FOUNDED THE COMPANY WILL
NOT HAVE TO TESTIFY IN COURT
MEMBERS OF THE FAMILY SAID WHILE
THE AGREEMENT ANNOUNCED TODAY IS
NOT A FINANCIAL MODEL FOR FUTURE
SETTLEMENT DISCUSSIONS, THE
ESTABLISHMENT OF THE NATIONAL
CENTER IS A UNIQUE AND IMPORTANT
STEP THAT WE HOPE WILL SAVE
LIVES.
PURDUE REPORTEDLY FACES UP TO
1600 CASES IN THE OPIOID CRISIS,
INCLUDING 37 STATES WHICH HAVE
SUED THE COMPANY SINCE 2017.
THE COMPANY HAS DENIED
WRONGDOING SAYING LABELS FOR ITS
PAIN KILLER CARRIED WARNINGS
ABOUT THE RISK OF ABUSE AND
MISUSE
EARLIER THIS MONTH THE PURDUE
CEO SAID THE COMPANY IS LOOKING
AT POSSIBLE BANKRUPTCY SAS A
RESULT OF THESE CLAIMS
TODAY'S SETTLEMENT LEAVES CLAIMS
PENDING JOHNSON & JOHNSON AND
ISRAEL-BASED TEVA
PHARMACEUTICALS.
>> ROBERT FRANK IS HERE WITH A
LOOK AT THE FATE OF THE FAMILY'S
MASSIVE FORTUNE.
>> YES, THEY ARE WORTH THAN
ESTIMATED $13 BILLION.
THEY HAVE GIVEN HUNDREDS OF
MILLIONS TO MUSEUMS AND
CHARITIES AROUND THE WORLD BUT
NOW THE FAMED SACKLER FAMILY IS
UNDER SIEGE FOR ITS ROLE
THE $270 MILLION SETTLEMENT IN
OKLAHOMA TODAY INVOLVED $75
MILLION PERSONALLY FROM THE
SACKLER FAMILY ITSELF.
THAT'S A SMALL PRICE GIVEN THAT
COURT DOCUMENTS SHOW THEY EARNED
$4 BILLION FROM PURDUE PHARMA
BETWEEN 2008 AND 2016, BUT THE
COSTS COULD ESCALATE
AS ADITI MENTIONED, THERE ARE
1600 OTHER LAWSUITS WAITING FOR
TRIAL.
FOR YEARS THE FAMILY HAS ARGUED
THAT THEY WERE MERELY PASSIVE
INVESTORS IN PURDUE.
BUT THE DOCUMENTS IN THE
MASSACHUSETTS CASE FILED
REVEALED THE FAMILY WAS ACTIVELY
INVOLVED IN DECISIONS RELATING
TO OXYCONTIN
MUSEUMS AND CHARITY GROUPS
REFUSING FURTHER GIFTS FROM THE
FAMILY, EVEN LOOKING AT POSSIBLY
RETURNING FUNDS.
THE TATE MUSEUMS IN LONDON AND
GUGGENHEIM IN NEW YORK SAID THEY
WOULD NOT ACCEPT FURTHERGIFTS
FROM THE FAMILY.
THE LOUVRE AND METROPOLITAN
MUSEUM OF SCIENCE HAVE ALSO
RECEIVED DONATIONS BUT THEIR
FORTUNE WILL LIKELY REMAIN
INTACT BECAUSE THEIR NET WORTH
IS SPREAD OUT OVER A MUCH LARGER
GROUP OF COMPANIES
THEY HAVE OTHER CORPORATE
INVESTMENTS AND THERE IS STILL A
PERCEPTION THAT EVEN IF THEY
FILE FOR BANKRUPTCY FOR THE
COMPANY, THAT WILL CREATE A
FIREWALL BETWEEN THESE SUITS AND
THEIR PERSONAL FORTUNE.
>> BUT THIS $75 MILLION THEY
HAVE GIVEN SO FAR WAS OF THEIR
OWN WILL, IT WASN'T PART OF THE
SETTLEMENT ITSELF.
THEY DECIDED TO GIVE THAT, THE
FAMILY
>> WELL, IT'S UNCLEAR WHETHER
THAT WAS A VOLUNTARY DECISION,
BUT IT NOW SETS PRECEDENT THAT
THEY ARE PARTICIPATING IN THE
SETTLEMENTS.
THEY PAID AS PART OF THE
SETTLEMENT AND THAT COULD SET
PRECEDENT FOR THE OTHER CASES.
THAT'S SORT OF AN ADMISSION THAT
THEY WERE IN SOME WAY INVOLVED
IN THIS.
>> IT'S INTERESTING, I WAS GOING
TO SAY THESE MUSEUMS REFUSING
THESE DONATIONS.
IF YOU GO BACK FAR ENOUGH, A LOT
OF THESE FORTUNES WERE BUILT ON,
WHO KNOWS, QUESTIONABLE
ACTIVITIES.
>> SURE.
AND THERE WERE MANY CHURCHES
THAT REFUSED TO ACCEPT JOHN D.
ROCKEFELLER'S MONEY BECAUSE THEY
SAID HE WAS ENGAGING IN
MONOPOLISTIC BEHAVIOR.
BUT IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME SINCE
WE'VE SEEN ANYBODY -- AMIDST ALL
THESE CRISIS AND SCANDAL OF ANY
INSTITUTION SAYING WE'RE NOT
GOING TO TAKE YOUR MONEY, THIS
IS THE FIRST WE'VE SEEN IN
DECADES.
>> I WAS LOOKING AT THE
SMITHSONIAN WHO HAS A SACKLER
GALLERY.
THEY ARE CONTRACTUALLY BOUND TO
KEEP THAT NAME.
>> AND THE SACKLER FAMILY TRUST
SAYING TODAY THEY ARE PUTTING A
TEMPORARY PAUSE ON ANY GIFTS TO
ANYONE UNTIL THIS IS RESOLVED.
>> ROBERT, THANKS VERY MUCH.
>>> WEWORK IS WORKING HARD IN
THE SHARING ECONOMY BUT DESPITE
RAPID EXPANSION AND INCREASE IN
REVENUES, IT LOOKS LIKE THEY
HAVE TO WORK HARDER TO BECOME
PROFITABLE AS AN IPO
THAT STORY IS AHEAD.
>>> BUT FIRST, PODCASTS ARE ON
OUR RADAR AS SPOTIFY CONTINUES
TO BE AGGRESSIVE IN THAT SCEPA
WE'LL TELL YOU WHAT THE
STREAMING GIANT IS UP TO NOW,
NEXT
erything.
No not everything,
I mean you're still blatantly
sucking up to me Gary.
Brilliantly observed, sir.
Always three steps ahead.
Six steps ahead. Sixteen.
So many steps.
You done?
A million steps ahead.
ServiceNow. Works for you.
See that's funny, I thought
you traded options.
I'm not really a
Wall Street guy.
What's the hesitation?
Eh, it just feels too
complicated, you know?
Well sure, at first, but JJ can
help you with that.
JJ, will you break it down for
this gentleman?
Hey, Ian. You know, at TD
Ameritrade, we can walk you
through your options
trades step by step
until you're comfortable.
I could be up for that.
That's taking options trading
from Wall St. to Main St.
Hey guys, wanna play some pool?
Eh, I'm not really a pool guy.
What's the hesitation?
It's just complicated.
Step-by-step options trading
support from TD Ameritrade
>>> WELCOME BACK
HERE ARE SOME OF THE OTHER
STORIES ON THE "CLOSING BELL"
TODAY.
I WENT WITH McDONALD'S
ACQUISITION OF DYNAMIC YIELD
IT'S PART OF THEIR PLAN TO
INCORPORATE MORE TECHNOLOGY IN
THEIR LOCATIONS.
THEY WILL ASSIST IN UPDATING THE
DIGITAL DRIVE-THROUGH MENUS TO
CHANGE DEPENDING ON DIFFERENT
FACTORS, LIKE THE WEATHER.
THE COMPANY'S LARGEST
ACQUISITION IN 20 YEARS,
REPORTEDLY VALUED AT MORE THAN
$300 MILLION
I ALWAYS FIND IT INTERESTING HOW
FAST FOOD RESTAURANTS ARE
GETTING MORE AND MORE INTO
TECHNOLOGY, WHETHER USING MORE
ROBOTICS AND AUTOMATING THEIR
MENUS.
IT SEEMS LIKE A PRETTY OBVIOUS
THING TO GIVE YOU CHOICES BASED
ON PREFERENCES OR WEATHER.
>> AND TO MAKE IT MORE EFFICIENT
BECAUSE THEY HAVE TO GET MORE
VOLUME THROUGH EACH DOOR.
>> ELECTRONIC ORDERING IS NOT
THAT EFFICIENT I FIND.
>> YOU HAVE TO GO TO ALL THE
MENUS.
>> IT GOES IN, TAKES A BIT OF
TIME AND IT'S NOT THAT
INSTANTANEOUS WHEN YOU GO TO
COLLECT IT
USUALLY A MORNING COFFEE WHEN I
GO TO McDONALD'S.
>> NOT A McMUFFIN?
NO HASH BROWNS, REALLY
>>> WAYFAIR IS GOING FROM ONLINE
TO OFFLINE
THEY PLAN TO OPEN THEIR FIRST
FULL-SERVICE STORE IN
MASSACHUSETTS LATER THIS YEAR.
SHOPPERS CAN PURCHASE PRODUCTS
IN STORE TO TAKE HOME OR PLACE
ORDERS FOR HOME DELIVERY
WAYFAIR PLANS TO OPEN FOUR
POP-UP LOCATIONS THIS SUMMER
THIS MAKES MORE SENSE BECAUSE
YOU CAN REALLY GO AND VIEW AND
EXPERIENCE THE FURNITURE
YOU PROBABLY WON'T TAKE IT HOME
UNDER YOUR ARM DEPENDING ON WHAT
THE ITEM IS.
BUT OF ALL THOSE ONLINE STORES,
IT SEEMS MORE --
>> WE'VE HAD THE WAYFAIR CEO ON
SO MANY TIMES.
WE ASK HIM WHY ARE PEOPLE GOING
TO BUY FURNITURE ONLINE WITHOUT
TRYING IT OUT IN STORE
HE SAID BECAUSE THE PRICES ARE
BETTER AND WE PUT SUCH A GOOD
JOB PUTTING IT OUT.
>> AND THEY HAVE A REPUTATION
FOR BEING DECENT PRODUCTS SO
PEOPLE WILL TAKE THE LEAP.
>> IT'S GOOD QUALITY.
>> EVEN IF YOU GO TO A TRA
TRADITIONAL FURNITURE STORE,
YOU'RE JUST SEEING A FLOOR
MODEL.
>> I DO THINK IT'S GOOD NEWS FOR
THOSE WHO SAY RETAIL IS NOT
DYING.
THE E-COMMERCE FOLKS HAVE TO GET
INTO RETAIL AS WELL.
>> IF IT'S MORE EFFICIENT TO DO
IT THAT WAY, THEY'LL TRY IT.
>>> SPOTIFY ANNOUNCING PLANS TO
BUY A PODCAST COMPANY, PAR CAST.
IT'S THE STREAMING GIANT'S 30
ACQUISITION OF A PODCAST COMPANY
WITHIN THE LAST TWO MONTHS
TERMS OF THE DEAL WERE NOT
DISCLOSED BUT SPOTIFY EXPECTS TO
SPEND $500 MILLION ON TOTAL
ACQUISITIONS THIS YEAR
SPOTIFY AT SOME POINT WAS
TALKING ABOUT ORIGINAL
PROGRAMMING.
THEY'LL GET KNEESTHESE EXCLUSIV
IT SEEMS LIKE PODCASTS IS AN
AREA YOU COULD DO THAT
ALSO I IMAGINE SOMEBODY'S
PODCAST LISTENING HABITS ARE
GOING TO TELL YOU A GOOD DEAL
ABOUT THEIR INTERESTS AND,
THEREFORE, AD TARGETING AND
THINGS LIKE THAT.
>> AND PODCASTS IN GENERAL GOING
FORWARD ARE PROBABLY CHEAPER FOR
THEM NOT TO ACQUIRE THE
COMPANIES PER SE, BUT BUYING THE
RIGHTS TO THE SONGS, WHICH WE
KNOW IS GREAT FOR THEM.
>> ALSO ANOTHER PIECE OF
EVIDENCE THAT CONTENT IS KING
RIGHT NOW.
LOOK AT APPLE YESTERDAY.
LOOK AT HOW MANY SCRIPTED SHOWS
ARE IN THE WORKS AND HOW TOP
DOLLAR THAT THEY'RE GETTING.
>> AND THEY'RE TRYING TO GO
WHERE PEOPLE ARE SPENDING THEIR
DIGITAL TIME
IF YOU LISTEN TO A 40-MINUTE
PODCAST, THAT'S TEN SONGS THAT
YOU DIDN'T LISTEN TO ON SPOTIFY
DURING THAT PERIOD.
>>> WE HAVE SOME NEWS ON BOEING.
PHIL LeBEAU IS JOINING US ON THE
PHONE WITH MORE ON THAT.
HI, PHIL.
>> HEY, WILF, ANY TIME YOU HAVE
SOMETHING GOING ON RIGHT NOW
WITH THE BOEING 737 MAX IT'S
GOING TO GET A LOT OF ATTENTION
AND THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENED THIS
AFTERNOON.
WITHIN THE LAST HOUR, THERE WAS
AN EMERGENCY LANDING OF A
SOUTHWEST AIRLINES BOEING 737
MAX PLANE IN ORLANDO, FLORIDA.
THIS WAS A PLANE THAT WAS IN
ORLANDO AND IT WAS ON A FLIGHT
TO BE STORED IN VICTORVILLE,
CALIFORNIA, THAT'S WHERE
SOUTHWEST IS PARKING THESE
PLANES WHILE THEY ARE OFFICIALLY
GROUNDED BY THE FAA.
THERE WAS AN ENGINE ISSUE
SHORTLY AFTER THEY TOOK OFF, SO
THEY RADIOED THE TOWER
THEY CAME AROUND, DID AN
EMERGENCY LANDING.
RELATIVE TO WHAT PEOPLE THINK OF
WHEN THEY THINK OF EMERGENCY
LANDING, THIS WAS NOT A HUGE
DEAL
I TALKED WITH SOME PEOPLE AT THE
FAA AND THEY SAID LOOK,
RELATIVELY SPEAKING, THIS WAS
A -- THEY CAME AROUND, SAW AN
ISSUE, THEY LANDED
MORE IMPORTANTLY AND SOMETHING
PEOPLE NEED TO KEEP IN MIND AS
THEY LOOK AT SHARES OF BOEING,
IT WAS UNRELATED TO THE REASONS
WHY THE 737 MAX IS CURRENTLY
GROUNDED BY THE FAA.
AGAIN, THIS WAS AN ENGINE ISSUE
ON A FERRY FLIGHT THAT HAD
NOTHING TO DO WITH THE ISSUES
THAT CAUSED THE GROUNDING OF THE
737 MAX BY THE FAA
>> NO PASSENGERS ONBOARD, PHIL
>> NO PASSENGERS ONBOARD
FOUR PEOPLE, FLIGHT CREW
THEY'RE MOVING IT OUT THERE
WHERE THEY'RE PARKING ALL OF
THEIR 737 MAXES WHILE THEY'RE
GROUNDED.
>> OKAY, FILL, THANKS VERY MUCH
FOR THAT
THE STOCK DOWN 1% AS WE SPEAK.
>>> WEWORKS' RAPID EXPANSION
LAST YEAR CAME WITH A HEFTY
PRICE.
WHY THE COMPANY'S LOSSES DOUBLED
TO NEAR LOW $2 BILLION
THAT'S UP NEXT
>>> THE SENATE HOLDING A
PROCEDURAL VOTE ON THE GREEN NEW
DEAL.
>> Reporter: WELL, THE
RESOLUTION ON THE GREEN NEW DEAL
DOES NOT HAVE ENOUGH SUPPORT TO
PASS THE SENATE.
CURRENTLY THE VOTE STANDS AT 57
VOTING NO AND NONE VOTING YES.
DEMOCRATS WERE LARGELY EXPECTED
TO VOTE PRESENT TO AVOID HAVING
TO GO ON THE RECORD EITHER FOR
OR AGAINST THIS CONTROVERSIAL
PROPOSAL, BUT THERE WERE A FEW
NOTABLE EXCEPTIONS
SENATORS KRISTEN CINEMA, DOUG
JONES AND JOE MANCHIN, THREE
DEMOCRATS THAT VOTED NO.
ALSO INDEPENDENT SENATOR ANGUS
KING ALSO A NO
DEM BEEN CALLING THIS A SHAM
VOTE
EVEN REPRESENTATIVE ALEXANDRIA
OCASIO-CORTEZ WHO ORIGINALLY
SPONSORED THIS IDEA SAID THAT
THIS IS JUST REPUBLICANS PLAYING
POLITICS
OF COURSE REPUBLICANS SAY THAT
DEMOCRATS SHOULD BE WILLING TO
TAKE A STAND ON A PROPOSAL THAT
THEY AT LEAST PAID LIP SERVICE
TO
AS OF NOW, IT LOOKS LIKE THE
RESOLUTION ON THE GREEN NEW DEAL
HAS NOW OFFICIALLY FAILED TO
ADVANCE IN THE SENATE.
BACK OVER TO YOU
>> SO DOES THAT MEAN, YLAN, THAT
IT'S DONE OR ARE WE GOING TO
CONTINUE TO HEAR ABOUT THIS AND
IS IT GOING TO CONTINUE TO BE A
CAMPAIGN TOPIC
>> Reporter: YOU'LL TEN TO HEAR
ABOUT IT EVEN THOUGH THIS VOTE
IN THE SENATE IS OVER AND THIS
IS NOT GOING TO GO ANYWHERE.
BUT CERTAINLY THIS IS STILL
SOMETHING THAT IS GOING TO PLAY
A LARGE ROLE IN THE 2020
PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN.
AS YOU HEARD SOME REPORTS THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID TODAY HE
HOPES THAT THE GREEN NEW DEAL
STAYS ALIVE SO THAT HE CAN
CAMPAIGN AGAINST IT.
>> OKAY, YLAN, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH FOR THAT.
TE> UP NEXT, WHAT WEWORKS'
LAST REVENUE AND LOSS NUMBERS
COULD MEAN FOR ITS IPO
WE'LL BE BACK IN A COUPLE OF
MINUTES.
to unlock opportunities
other advisers might not see.
Learn what a CFA Charterholder
can do for you,
at therightquestion.org
♪ ♪ ♪
MOVE TO THE
ENTERPRISE-GRADE CLOUD
THAT'S BUILT TO
HANDLE ALL YOUR APPS.
♪ ♪ ♪
THE IBM CLOUD.
THE CLOUD FOR SMARTER BUSINESS.
What do advisors look for
in an ETF?
I tell clients, ETFs can
follow an index,
but which ones
target your goals?
It's not about quantity.
It's about quality.
No trendy stuff.
I want ETFs backed by research.
Is it built for the long-term?
My reputation depends on it.
FlexShares ETFs
are designed and managed around
investor objectives.
So you can advise
with confidence.
Before investing, consider the
fund's investment objectives,
risks, charges and expenses.
Go to flexshares.com
for a prospectus
containing this information.
Read it carefully.
Does your wealth
manager measure up?
A CFA Charterholder does.
They have the
investment expertise
you need for the ambitions
you have for your wealth.
Learn what a CFA Charterholder
can do for you,
at therightquestion.org
>>> WORK SPACE SETUP WEWORK,
WHILE REVENUE JUMPED LAST YEAR,
IT WASN'T ALL GOOD NEWS.
DEIDRE BOSA HAS THE BREAKDOWN
ISN'T SAN FRANCISCO.
>> HEY, WILF, THAT'S EXACTLY
RIGHT.
REVENUE MAY HAVE DOUBLED TO $1.8
BILLION SO SO DID ITS LOSSES
THEY WERE EVEN HIGHER AT $2
BILLION.
WHILE THAT IS A HUGE NUMBER,
IT'S NOT ACTUALLY VERY UNUSUAL
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE OTHER BIG
STARTUPS GETTING READY TO TAP
PUBLIC MARKETS
BURNING THROUGH CASH IN FAVOR OF
GROWTH IS PAR FOR THE COURSE
THESE DAYS
LYFT'S LOSSES WERE NORTH OF $900
MILLION LAST YEAR.
UBER'S LOSS, $1.8 BILLION.
PINTEREST'S LOSSES WERE ONLY IN
THE TENS OF MILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
ZOOM'S S-1 WAS REMARKABLE
BECAUSE THE COMPANY IS ACTUALLY
PROFITABLE
WEWORKS' VICE CHAIRMAN, MICHAEL
GROSS, TELLING ME THERE ARE A
NUMBER OF LEVERS THAT COULD BE
LESS UNPROFITABLE BUT DOING SO
WOULD COME AT THE EXPENSE OF
GROWTH AND THEY DON'T WANT TO DO
THAT
THEY'RE WATCHING THE UPCOMING
GRAUP OF IPOs CLOSELY AND THE
NEXT WEEK WILL BE CRITICAL AND
THE LIFTS AHEAD.
LYFT IS EXPECTED TO DEBUT THIS
FRIDAY, UBER AS EARLY AS APRIL
PRIVATE MARKETS THAT ARE FLUSH
WITH CAPITAL HAVE LED THESE
COMPANIES' VALUATIONS HIGHER AND
HIGHER
WE'LL SEE IF PUBLIC MARKET
INVESTORS VALUE GROWTH OVER
PROFITS AS WELL OR IF THESE
RIDE-SHARING COMPANIES AND
OTHERS END UP MORE LIKE SNAP AND
GROUPON, OTHER TECH DARLINGS
THAT WENT PUBLIC WITH NO PROFITS
AND HAVE STRUGGLED IN THE
AFTERMATH.
GUYS.
>> DEED REMARKS I GUESS LYFT IS
AN EXAMPLE WHERE DESPITE A
WIDENING LOSS, THE MARKET STILL
HAPPY TO GET ONBOARD AND THE
INDICATIONS ARE THAT'S EVEN
GOING TO GO ABOVE THE EARLIER
INDICATED RANGE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE DID HAVE A SOURCE TELL US
THAT IT'S GOING TO BE PRICING
ABOVE ITS EXPECTED RANGE
REMEMBER, THAT ITS LESS PRIVATE
MARKET VALUATION WAS $16
BILLION.
IT'S ALREADY RAISED BILLIONS OF
DOLLARS.
IT IS EXPECTED TO GO PUBLIC
LATER THIS WEEK AT A VALUATION
NORTH OF $23 BILLION
THAT'S A HUGE JUMP
UBER, THE JUMP IS EXPECTED TO BE
EVEN HIGHER.
WE KNOW IN THE LEAD-UP TO ITS
IPO, UBER IS SHORING UP
BUSINESSES AND POTENTIALLY EVEN
TAKING MORE INVESTMENT.
>> DEIDRE, STAY WITH US.
MIKE AS A CONVERSATION ON THE
IPO PIPELINE AND THE FACT THAT
MANY OF THESE COMPANIES HAVE
VERY QUICKLY GROWING REVENUES
AND ALSO GIANT LOSSES.
>> YEAH, WE'VE SEEN VERY HOT IPO
MARKETS BEFORE, BUT MOSTLY IT
WAS AN AWFUL LOT OF SMALLER
DEALS OF COMPANIES IN THE EARLY
STAGES
PRETTY MUCH UNPRECEDENTED TO
HAVE ALL OF THESE MULTI BILLION
DOLLAR PRIVATE MARKET VALUATIONS
KIND OF HEADING FOR THE PUBLIC
MARKET EXIT AT ONCE.
DEIDRE IS RIGHT, IN TERMS OF
TESTING THE PUBLIC MARKET'S
TOLERANCE FOR TRUSTING THAT
THESE COMPANIES ARE GOING TO GET
TO A CERTAIN SCALE OR FIND THE
WAY TO THEIR NEXT ACT THAT'S
GOING TO BE PROFITABLE, TO BE
HONEST, THESE ARE NOT COMPANIES
IF YOU TALK ABOUT LYFT, WEWORK,
UBER, DOOR DASH, AND OTHER
DELIVERY COMPANIES ARE PAYING
PEOPLE TO DRIVE THINGS AROUND.
THESE ARE OLD BUSINESSES TRYING
IT IN A NEW WAY.
THAT'S WHY I WONDER IF THE
PUBLIC WILL GIVE A BIG PREMIUM
TO THE PRIVATE MARKET
VALUATIONS.
>> DEIDRE, JUST QUICKLY, THE
OTHER FACTOR WE WONDERED, WOULD
THERE BE A PUSHBACK ON THE
STRUCTURES OR EVEN A CONCERN
WHEN THE S-1s SAY WE MAY NEVER,
EVER BE PROFITABLE AN IT SEEMS
PEOPLE DON'T MIND.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU HAD PINTEREST SAY IT WAS
GOING TO DO A DUAL STRUCTURE
LYFT'S FOUNDERS ARE EXPECTED TO
REMAIN ALMOST MAJORITY CONTROL
SOME ARGUE IF YOU DON'T WANT THE
DUAL STRUCTURE DON'T GO WITH A
LYFT, GO WITH AN UBER THAT WILL
HAVE A ONE VOTE STRUCTURE.
IT WILL BE INTERESTING TO SEE
HOW THEY PERFORM INSPECT TERMS
OF WHO HAS THAT STRUCTURE AND
WHO DOESN'T BECAUSE THIS HAS
IMPORTANT INDICATIONS. OF ATTORE
FAMILIAR WITH, DO THE PAPERWOR E
FAMILIAR WITH, DO THE PAPERWOR
UNLOCK, YOU KNOW, THE
SUBSCRIPTIONS OF THE WORLD FOR
THEIR PRODUCTS SO I DO THINK IT
MAKES SENSE AND THE WORLIS BIG
ENOUGH FOR MULTIPLE OF THESE
THINGS AND AS I WAS SAYING
BEFORE, IT'S NOTOR BREAK
FOR APPLE.
THEY CAN PLAY THE LONG GAME, BE
IN THE MARKETS AND SEE HOW IT
DEVELOPS WITEIR CUSTOMER
RELATIONSHIPS.
>> ANOTHER ONE TO WATCH, AFTER
ALL THE DRAMA AND BACK AND
FORTH, NIKE CLOSEDHE DAY
HIGHER AFTER THAT SHARP DROP ON
THE AVENATTI TWEET
BEFORE HE WAS TAKEN INTO
CUSTODY.
WHAT A WEIRD STORY.
>> THAT DOES IT FOR TODAY.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
>> "FAST MONEY" BEGINS RIGHT
NOW.
>>> "FAST MONEY" STARTS RIGHT
NOW LIVE FROM THE NASDAQ MARKET
SITE IN NEW YORK CITY'S TIMES
SQUARE
I'M SCOTT WAPNER IN FOR MELISS
LEE.
TIM SEYMOUR, STEVE GRASSO, DAN
NATHAN AND GUY ADAMI
AHEAD ON "FAST," FINANCIALS
UNDER FIRE
THE GROUP SINKING DEEPER INTO
CORRECTION AS THE TEN-YEAR YLD
HITS ITS LOWEST LEVEL SINCE 2017
AND THE TOP CHNICIAN SAYS
THERE'S MORE PAIN COMING AND
WHAT TO BUY INSTEAD.
THE DOW ON TRACK FOR ITS FIRST
DOWN MONTH OF THE YEAR
MORE VOLATILITY,UY SAYS THIS
STOCK RIGHT HERE COULD BE ABOUT
TO BREAK OUT BUT WE START WHERE
ELSEAPPLE.
HOSTING A STAR-STUDDED EVENT
WITH A NEW STREAMING SERVICE,
GAMING SERVICES AND CREDIT CARD.
JOSH LIPTON HAS MORE FROM
CUPERTINO.
>> THE STAR OF THE SHOW HAD TO
BE THAT NEW VIDEO STREG
SERVICE.
IT'S CALLED APPLE TV PLUS.
>> WE PARTNERED WITH THE MOST
THOUGHTFUL ACCOMPLISHED AND
AWARD-WINNING GROUP OF CREATIVE
VISIONARIES WHO HAVE EVER COME
TOGETHER IN ONE PLACE  CREATE
A NEW SERVICE UNLIKE ANYTHING
THAT'S BEEN DONE BEFORE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
APPLE TV PLUS.
>> SO THIS NEW SERVICE, SCOTT,
WILL FEATURE ORIGINAL SHOW,
MOVIES AND DOCUMENTARIES FROM
HOLLYWOOD SUPERSTARS WHO WE
HERE TODAY TALKING ABOUT THEIR
NEW SHOWS, SO YOU SAW STEVEN
SPIELBERG, REESE WITHERSPOON,
JENNIFER AN 'TIS STO-- ANISTON D
OPRAH.
WHAT IS THE PRICE GOING TO BE OF
THIS SERVICE
WE'LL HAVE TO WAIT TORE THAT
DIONLY APPLE DEBUTED AN
CAN SCRIBE TO HBO, SHOWTIME AND
STARZ AND NEWS PLUS, A NEW
SUBSCRIPTION SERVICE BRINGING
OVER 300 MAGAZINES ANDEANG
NEWSPAPERS FOR 9.99, AN APPLE
CARD WHICH IS A NEW CARD BUILT
INTO THE APPLE ON THE iPHONE AS
WELL AS A PHYSICAL CREDIT CARD
DESIGNED TO WORK WHERE APPLE PAY
IS NOT ACCEPTED AND FINALLY
APPLE DID TEASE A NERVICE
FOR GAMERS AS WELL
IT'S GOING TO BE APPLE CAR CADE.
A SUBSCRIPTION SERVICE THAT WILL
FEATUROVER 100 NEW AND
EXCLUSIVE GAMES THAT ALSO
LAUNCHING IN THE FALL.
APPLE, OF UR, DOES BOTH A
HUGE INSTALL BASE, 1.4 BILLION
APPLE DEVICES OUT THERE SO HOW
MANY FANS CAN NOW APPLE CONVINCE
TO BUY IN TO THESE NEW SERVICES
VEILED TODAY
SCOTT, BACK TO YOU
> THANKS SO MUCH
APPLE SHARES CLOSING DOWN MORE
THAN 1%.
STILL UP AROUND 20% THIS YEAR,
SO WILL THE COMPANY'S
TRSFORMATION TO SERVICES PAY
OFF FOR INVESTORS?
THAT'S THE KEY QUESTION.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS ABOUT.
>> IT IS
THE STOCK IS UP 33% FROM JANUARY
2nd WHEN THE COMPANY
PREANNOUNCED PRETTY
DISAPPOINTING SCAL QUARTER
A LOT HAD TO DO WITH HARDWARE
AND WEAKNESS IN CHINA.
IF YOU CAN OVERLOOK ALL THAT AND
LOOK AT THE ANNOUNCEMENTS THEY
MADE TODAY WHILE THERE WASN'T A
WHOLE HECK OF A LOT OF DETAIL,
PRICG, THAT SORT OF THING,
WHEN THE PRODUCTS ARE GOING TO
BE RELEASED CAN YOU THINK ABOUT
THAT INSTALL BASE AND THE FACT
THAT THE AVERAGE iPHONE USER
SPENDS $44 ON -- YOU KNOW,
ANNUALLY ON THEIR -- THROUGH
THEIR DEVICE IN THIS ECOSYSTEM
AND THAT'S A WHOLE HOST OF
SERVICES THAT THEY'LL BE ABLE TO
EXPAND THAT ECOSYSTEM.
IT'S NOT A REASON TO BUY AT 188
BUCKS UP 33% FROM THOSE 52-WEEK
LOWS BUT SOMETHING THAT SHOULD
GIVE YOU SOLACE ABOUT THE FUTURE
OF THE COMPANY AS THEY TRY TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO OFFSET UNIT
DECLINES AND WHAT WILL
ULTIMATELY DECLINING MARGINS IN
THE HARDWARE BUSINESS.
>> TIMMY, DAN SAID IT.
NOT ENOUGH TO BUY THE STOCK.
IS THAT RIGHT?
>> AT 14 1/2 X TIMES CASH PUTS
YOU AROUND 220, 225.
I OWN THE STOCK.
I THINK IT'S WORTH OWNING
INDEPENDENT OF TODAY'S
ANNOUNCEMENT
I THINK I AGREE WITH DAN.
>> DO YOU BUY  FRE HERE?
>> YEAH, I CAN PUT FRESH CAPITAL
WORK HERE.
>> NOTHING BLUE YOU OUT OF THE
WATER.
THE SELL-OFF IS ABSURD
IF THAT'S WHY IT SOLD OFF, IT
FAILED AT 200.
>> MOVING DOWN INTO THE EVENT
ANYWAY.
>> THAT'S THE --
>> I MEAN TODAY, I MEAN.
>> THE GO TO ACTION.
YOU SELL IT BASICALLY ON THE
EVENT AND CHECK THE BOX AND DID
ENOUGH TO MAKE IT INTERESTING.
BUT IT'S NOT KILLING NETFLIX
PRICE ACTION SHOWS THAT.
IT'S HELPING ROKU.
I THINK THEY DID ENOUGH WITH
LEAVING --
SORRY
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
>> PRICE ACTION IN ROKU.
BENEFITS THEM, TAILWIND.
PRICE ACTION IN NETFLIX, NOT A
NETFLIX KILLER BUT APPLE IS NOT
A --
>> IT WILL BE INCLUDED SO APPLE
WILL BE INCLUDED ON ROKU'S
PLATFORM.
>> GUY, ATO YOU THINK,
CREDIT CARD, THE TV, THE CREDIT
CARD --
>> WELCOME
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU HERE.
>> YOU'RE ALWAYS WELCOMING
>> WELCOME BACK.
LET'S GET THOSE PLEASANTRIES OUT
OF THE WAY.
>> IT'S NICE.
>> LISTEN --
>> BACK TO THE MATTER AT HAND.
>> IT WAS A PRETTY INTERESTING
ANNOUNCEME GTING AWAY FROM
THE HARDWARE SIDE AND THINK IT'S
INTERESTING.
CREDIT CARD, PEOPLE WILL SAY,
NOA BIG DEAL
FOR A LOT OF MILLENNIALS IT
MIGHT BE
THEY'RE WORKING ON THAT INSTALL
BASE WITHOUT QUESTION.
IN TERMS OF THE STOCK, THOUGH,
ALL-TIME HIGH 232 OR SO IN
SEPTEMBER.
TRADED DOWN TO 1 -- WHAT WAS IT
142-ISH ON DECEMBER 24th
IF YOU LOOK AT THE 50%
RETRACEMENT PUTS YOU EXACTLY
WHERE IT'S TRADING RIGHT NOW
I HAPPEN TO WATCH THE "SQUAWK
BOX" WITH JOE KERNEN
HE INTERVIEWED JIM CRAMER.
NOT THAT I'M TRYING TO CURRY
FAVOR WITH JIM, JIM WAS DISMAYED
IT WAS HIGHER IN THE PREMARKET
SAYING IT WAS PERFECT TO SEL
OFF.
HE WAS RIGHT
I THINK IT BACKS OFFER
NOT TO SPAS ASPERSIONS AT APPLE.
I JUSTY IT'S RUN TOO FAR TO
>> I THOUGHT THAT WAS AN
INTERESTING THING.
SERVICE GROWTH IN THE QUARTER
WAS IN THE TEENS, YOU KNOW, IT'S
DECELERATED OFF OF WHAT WAS A
VERY SMALL BASE.
HIGHER GROWTH RATES AND 50% --
NOW THAT IT'S BECOME A $20
LLION ANNUAL BUSINESS AND
GROWING, IT'S MUCH LESS SO TO ME
I THINK THAT POINTING TO
SERVICES GROWTH IS NOT THE WHOLE
THING, YOU HAVE TO POINT TO THE
HIGHER MARGINS BUT YOU HAD A
GREAT DISCUSSION, THE HALFTIME
REPORT ON AT NOON EVERY DAY.
>> PROFESSIONAL.
>> BUT TONY SAID HE EXPECTS
UNITS TO BE DOWN 15% YEAR OVER
YEAR
THIS IS THE THIRD CONSECUTIVE
>> THAT'S REALLY --
>> YOU'LL NEED GREATER GROWTH
AND REALLY FAT MARGINS
THEY'RE SPLITTING --
>> IS IT ENOUGH?
>> IT AT LEAST GIVES YOU THE
CONVERSATION --
IT AT LEAST GIVES YOU THE
CONVERSATION AND GETS YOUR MIND
OFF THE HARDWARE BUSINESS THAT
IS SLUGGISH AND SLOWING AND
THINK ABOUT THE $40 BILLION
NUMBER
>> THEY SPENT TWO HOURS SPEAKING
TO THE ENTIRE WORLD ABOUT THIS
HUGE NEW OPPORTUNITY
WOULDN'T YOU LE WALL STREET
ANALYSTS TO COME OUT AND SAY
THIS IS GOING TO BE AN X AMOUNT
OF OPPORTUNITY
>> YEAH.
>> WE'LL --
>> THEY'RE NOT DOING THAT.
>> IF YOU THINK OF FIRST OF ALL
THE CREDIT CARD BUSINE, I
ACTUALLY THINK THAT IS SOMETHING
THAT ULTIMATELY COULD MOVE THE
NEEDLE
THE SERVICES BUSINESS, SORRY,
THE APPLE PLUS, THE TV PLUS AND
WHATEVER IS IN THAT BUNDLE AND
REALIZE THEY HAVE A FEW
HIGH-PROFILE CONTENT CREATOR ON
THEIR PLATFORM RIGHT NOW, LOOK,
IT'S GOING TO TAKE TIME.
THERE WAS NOTHING THEY COULD
HAVE TOLD THAWS WOULD HAVE
ANGED THE STORY.
THIS IS ABOUT A COMPANY
ALLOCATING RESOURCES TOWARD HIGH
MARGIN BUSINESSES AND AT THIS
POINT AND VALUATION WHY
SHOULDN'T WE BELIEVE APP
"JOURNAL" THEY'VE DELIVERED ON
EVERYTHING THEY WENT TO DO WITH
AN INCREDIBLY LOYAL CUSTOMER
BASE WHO -- THOSE GUYS PROBABLY
WANT --
FOR YEARS APPLE TV WAS
RELEASED EIGHT YEARS AGO OR
SOMETHING AND STEVE JOBS CALLED
IT A HOBBY
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN CATEGORIZED
THAT WAY
ROKU HAD A BIG DAY
>> EVERYTHING HAD A BIG DAY --
>> IT'S A VERY CONFUSING.
>> DOESN'T HAVE TO BE, DOES IT
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OFFERING
THIS COMPANY HAS EVER PUT OUT IN
E SOFTWARE UNIVERSE AT YOU
CAN GET WITHOUT THEIR HARDWARE
THERE'S SOME THINGS ON ANDROID
NOW.
ES ON THE ANDROID DEVICE
THAT IS A MASSIVE SHIFT FOR THE
COMPANY OVER THE 40-YEAR --
>> THEY HAVE TO.
>> I KNOW SO THE QUESTION IS,
THERE'S SO LITTLE DETAIL BIT
WHO KNOWS.
THIS MAY NOT B-- THE VIDEO
STREAMING BUSINESS MAY NOT --
>> IT WASN'T ENOUGH -- I'LL
SPEAK -- IT WASN'T ENOUGH FOR ME
TO SAY I'M ON BOARD.
FIRST OF ALL WE DON'T KNOW
PRICING OR WHAT THE OFFERING
WILL BE.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S ENOUGH
THERE BUT I DO OWN THE STOCK
I OWN IT FROM LOWER AND IF I OWN
TODAY. IS, IN EFFECT, BUYING IT
PUTTING NEW MONEY TO WORK
BECAUSE YOU'RE STILL STAYING
LONG SO I THINK THEY DID ENOUGH
TO PREOCCUPYPLE UNTIL WE GET
ALL THE DETAILS.
>> DOES IT GET YOU EXCITED ABOUT
WHAT THEY'RE DOING FROM THE
SERVICES STANDPOINT TO, AGAIN,
GROW THAT BUSINESS TO ENOUGH
SCALE TO OFFSET ANY SLOWDOWN IN
PHONES
>> LOOK.
>> AND HARDWARE.
>> DAN TALKED ABOUT HOW IT'S A
SMALL BASE SO THE EARLY GROWTH
NUMBERS OF THE DELTA WAS MORE
IMPRESSIVE A YEAR AND A HALF AGO
BUT IT'S STILL AN ABSOLUTE IN
TERMS OF AGGREGATE TERMS
MASSIVE.
I AM EXCITED ABOUT THE LOYALTY
AND ABOUT THE DIFFERENCE WAYS
THEY'RE MONETIZING
PEOPLE ARE COMMITTED TO APPLE
AND THEY'RE STUCK IF THEY'RE ON
TV AND I CAN PICK UP A KNICKS
GAME, $2.99 WON'T MEAN A LOT
A LOT BEHAVE THAT WAY WITH
APPLE.
>> THEY'RE NOT SAYING IT,
THEY'RE FOCUSING ON SERVICES AND
IT'S BECAUSE THEY SEE THE
DECELERATION IN HARDWARE
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO SAY THAT
BUT THEIR LASER FOCUS --
>> THEIR ACTIONS SPEAK LOUDER
THAN WORDS.
>> JINKS.
>> THE QUESTION, IS THE
SERVICE'S BUSINESS, ARE REVENUES
SLOWING TO THE POINT WHERE TIGHT
GO
-- IT'S GOING TO BE A
HINDRANCE?
YOU CAN'T HAVE SERVICE REVENUE
SLOWING AT THE SAME TIME THAT
HANDSET SALES ARE SLOWING?
>> IN ORDER TO GET THE VALUATION
THEY WANT THE PEOPLE ALONG THE
STOCK WATCH SERVICES REVENUE HAS
TO BE AROUND 20% TO 22%.
WHAT, ARE WE ABOUT 15%, 16%?
AND THAT IS GETTING SLOWER
TOWARDS THE UPSIDE
>> ONE POINT, IT'S REALLY
IMPORTANT.
YOU DON'T TEED TO HAVE HYPER
GROWTH
CAN YOU HAVE MIDTEENS GROWTH ON
A BUSINESS THAT'S, YOU KNOW,
THAT HAS MUCH HIGHER MARGINS
THAN THE HARDWARE BUSINESS
GREAT FOR THE OVERALL PIE.
THIS DOESN'T NEED TO BE A HYPER
GROWTH STORY BUT TAKING SOME OF
THE TOTAL ADDRESSABLE MARKET
THAT EXISTS AND GROWING IT ON
YOUR USER BASE THAT MAY NOT BE
USINOF SERVICES OF OTHER
PROVIDERS.
>> THE NEGATIVE WAY TO SPIN IT
FROM A PERSON LONG HOW MUCH ISTL
ABOUT TRYING TO STEM OR STOP THE
SLIDE IN HARDWARE SALES?
THEY'RE PUTTING AN AWFUL LOT OF
TIME INTO SERVICES
MAYBE THEY JUST CAN'T HANDLE THE
SLIDE -- THERE'S NOTHING TO DO
ABOUT THE HARDWARE SIDE WHICH
THEN BECOMES AN OVERWHELMING --
>> YOU HAVE TO TARGET YOUR
INSTALLED BASE, 1.BILLION
DEVICES IN THE UNIVERSE OUT
THERE.
>> I KNOW.
I'M THE INSTALL BASE TOO AND I
WASN'T OVERWHELMED BY THIS
THIS IS NOT GOING TO BE
SOMETHING THAT -- AT LEAST ALT
THIS POINT.
>> TIM WILL PLAY 3 BUCKS FOR A
KNICK GAME
>> THEY'RE WORTH A BUCK.
>> I WILL PAY 3 BUT THAT'S WHAT
PEOPLE DO ON THEIR iPHONES AND
THEY HAVE A CAPTIVE AUDIENCE
1.4 INSTALLED BASE
THE ULTIMATE IS PROBABLY 20
TIMES AS OPPOSED TO ABOUT 11
TIMES ON THE HARDWARE AND
SOMETHING PEOPLE FORGET ON A $4
BILLION -- IF.
>> YOU MENTIONED JAMIE DIMON
DIDN' -
CRAMER DIDN'T LIKE THE STOCK UP.
IT HAS RUN --
>> THIS STOCK USUALLY RUN HAS AN
EVENT AN SELLS OFFER
S
SAKINOCCI SAID ON THE SHOW --
>> THE MARKETPLACE TOLD YOU THE
VALUATION AND WEREN'T IMPRESSED
AND SOLD THE STOCK OFF AND ALL
RE RIVERALS WERE BOUGHT.
>> UP 10% IN A MONTH.
>> IT LAGGED THE MARKET TOO,
SCOTT.
THERE'S SOME PART THATENMENT
GOT SO PR AND PEOPLE WERE
LOOKING AT VALUATIONS AND APPLE
UNDERPERFORMED
>> MORE, CUPERTINO, GENE, YOU
WERE IN THE EVENT, I BELIEVE,
TODAY.
WHAT'S YOUR TAKEAWAY TONIGHT
>> SCOTT, REALLY TWO IMPACT.
IF YOU PUT THESE FOUR SERVICES
TOGETHER AND THINK ABOUT WHAT IT
COULD ADD IN THE NEXT FIVE YEARS
I THINK ABOUT A BILLION OR 20
BILLION OR SO IN REVENUE, THAT
PROBABLY EQUATES TO ABOUT 10% IN
"S
ANNUAL SERVICES GROWTHTHAT'SHE .
THEN I THINK THERE'S A HIGHER
LEVEL ORDER THAT APPLE IS
SHOOTING FOR THAT GETS LIN
THESE ANNOUNCEMENTS.
THEY'VE BEEN LARGELY ANTICIPATED
AND WHETHER OR NOT THE CONSUMERS
WANT THIS REMAINS TO BE SEEN BUT
EFFECTIVELY WHAT APPLE IS
SAYING, THEY'LL TAKE THINGS WE
INTERACT WITH EVERY DAY WHETHER
A SCREAMING SER-- STREAMING SERE
OR CREDIT CARD AND IT'S
ENRICHING PEOPLE'S LIVES AND I
RECOGNIZE WHEN I USE THAT
LANGUAGE IT MAKES ME FEEL LIKE
I'M JUST REPEATING WHAT THEIR
MESSAGE BUT I THINK IT IS AN
IMPORTANT DISTINCTION TRYING TO
CREATE CONTENT NOT ABOUT THE
TYPICACONTL T WE'VE SEEN, THIS
ENRICHED CONTENT, GAMING MORE
HEALTHY GAMING AND FIRST TIME A
CREDIT CARD CAN ACTUALLY ADD
TRANSPARENCY AND THAT GETS LOST
THE CONVERSATION TODAY.
THESE SUBTLE LITTLE APPROACHES
THAT APPLE DOES TO MAKE OUR
LIVES JUST A LITTLE BIT BETTER
AND I THINK THAT ULTIMATELY WILL
YIELD A HIGHER SHARE PRICE
I'M ENCOURAGED BY THE
ANNOUNCEMENT.
>> IT TAKES THE SERVICES
BUSINESS TO THE NEXT LEVEL, SO
TO SPEAK
>> YEAH, DEFINITELY ONHE VIDEO
SIDE, ON THE CREDIT CARD
WHAT THEY'RE DOING IS SOMETHING
THAT I THINK OTHER CREDIT CARDC
TRY TO ADD THAT LAYER OF
TRANSPARENCY
REALLY SHIFTING THE FOCUS FROM
MAKING MONEY AS AN ISSUER TO TRY
TO -- APPLE IS NOT GOING TO MAKE
A TON OF MONEY OFF THE CDIT
CARD
I WANT TO BE CLEAR ABOUT THAT.
THIS IN FIVE YEARS CAN BE CALL
IT A BILLION AND A HALF DOLLAR
BUSINESS, MUCH SMALLER THAN THE
$15 BILLION BUT THE INTERESTING
PART JUST TO GO ONE MORE LEVEL
DEEPER ON THE CREDIT CARD, THE
EXCITING PART, IF YOU LOOK AT
THE OTHER ANNOUNCEMENTS THERE
ARE VARIATIONS TO A BETTER
DEGREE THAWE'VE SEEN BEFORE
BUT THE CREDIT CARD, THAT
ACTUALLY WAS A MAMEASURABLE
I THINK THAT IS A GOOD EXAMPLE
OF WHAT AN ADVANTAGE THAT APPLE
HAS OF TYING TOGETHER THE
HARDWARE, SOFT AND SERVICES.
>> GENE, WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE
INVESTMENT THEY'RE PUTTING IN
AND TRYING TO BECOME A
COMPETITOR OF NETFLIX, WERE YOU
UNDERWHELMED BY THE AMOUNT OF
INVESTMENTS, SHOULD THAT BE 10X
OR THE FACT TO YOUR POINT IT'S
FOUR SERVICES SO THEY'RE TRYING
TO FOCUS ON ALL OF THEM AND NOT
JUST ONE OF THEM AND THEN MORE
OF AN AGGREGATOR VERSUS A DIRECT
COMPETITOR TO SO MANY SERVICES
THEY'RE OFFERING
>> I THINK THEY WANTED TO TRY TO
BUNDLE ALL THESE SERVICE
ANNOUNCEMENTS TOGETHER
A LOGICAL TIME OF THE YEAR TO DO
THAT
WHEN YOU DO THAT, YOU HAVE TO
PREANNOUNCE THINGS AND DON'T
HAVE A LOT OF DETAIL SO LET'S
TALK ABOUT THE VIDEO REAL
QUICKLY.
IT'S UNCLEAR HOW MANY SHOWS AND
MOVIES THEY HAVE
MOST LIKELY PROBABLY AROUND 40
WHICH IS A FAR CRY FROM NETFLIX
AT A THOUSAND ORIGINAL SERIES.
BUT I THINK THE QUALITY OF THIS
IS WHAT IS GOING TO ULTIMATELY
STAND OUT AND I SUSPECT THE WAY
APPLE WILL MEASURE THEIR SUCCESS
IS THE NUMBER OF INDTRY
AWARDS
I DON'T KNOW ENOUGH ABOUT
ENTERTAINMENT AND THE AWARDS
THEY'LL GUN FOR BUT AT THE
OF THE DAY THIS CONTENT, THIS
DIFFERENT APPROACH IS GOING TO
HAVE AN IMPACT AND THINK THAT
COULD BE A SIMILAR SIZE BUSINESS
AS NETFLIX CALLS IT, $15 BILLION
A YEAR
I AM IN THE CAMP IT WILL HAVE A
NEGATIVE IMPACT OVER THE NEXT
YEAR.
>> HOW DO YOU JUDGE THE STOCK
TODAY GIVEN THE FACT IT HAD SUCH
A BIG RUN INTO THE
ANNOUNCEMENTS?
>> I THINK IT'S A GREAT EXAMPLE
OF HOW THESE APPLE EVENTS SET
UP
WE GENERALLY KNOW WHAT'S
HAPPENING GOING INTO IT BUT THE
SIGNIFICANCE OF WHAT'S ANNOUNCED
REALLY DOESN'T BECOME MORE CLEAR
TO US UNTIL QUARTERS AND YEARS
AHEAAND I THINK I JUDGE THE
SIGNIFICANCE AS APPLE IS MAKING
A STATEMENT AND GOING AFTER
SERVICES BUT THEY'RE ALSO TAKING
A DIFFERENT APPROACH TO SERVICE.
THAT DIFFERENT APPROACH IS
ENRICHING LIVES AND MORE HEALTHY
GAME CONTENT
SO I VIEW THIS AS A POSITIVE IN
LINE WITH APPLE'S BRAND AND
MENTIONED SECURITY IF YOU'RE
INTERESTED AND PLAYING BUZZWORD
BINGO SEVEN TIMES THEY ARE HEAVY
ON THAT THEME AS WELL WHICH I
THINK IS SOMETHING UNIQUE APPLE
CAN ADD TO THESE SERVICE.
>> THIS MUST TAKE A DEAL FOR A
CONTENT COMPANY OFF THE TABLE.
>> WHAT WOULD -- WHAT WOD IT
TAKE TO -- I MISSED THAT.
>> I'M SAYING THESE KIND OF
ANNOUNCEMENTS WOULD TAKE A DEAL
FOR ANY KIND OF CONTENT COMPANY
BY APPLE OFF THE TABLE
>> I THINK LARGELY YOU'RE RIGHT
BECAUSE I THINK WHAT IT SHOWS
THEY WANT TO DO SOMETHING
DIFFERENT.
>> DO IT THEMSELVES.
>> I DON'T THINK THEY'LL ACQUIRE
NET FLISHGS.
CBS, THEY'LL ACQUIRE SOME TYPE
OF CONTENT
THEY WOULD HAVE TO KILL A LOT OF
THE CONTENT SO I THINK IT
LARGELY DOES TAKE THAT OFF THE
TABLE.
>> GENE, THANKS.
GOOD TO TALK TO YOU AS ALWAYS.
GUY.
>> BEGIN, GENE, HE NAILS IT.
50% RETRACEMENT OFF THE ALL-TIME
HIGH
THE 50 DAY MOVING AGE COMING
IN AROUND 175.
I THINK IT'S REASONABLE TO THINK
BEFORE EARNINGS ON APRIL 30th
APPLE RETESTS THAT 175 LEVEL.
>> I THINK THEY MISS THE MARKET
AS FAR AS VIDEO CONTENT.
THAT'S NOT WHY PEOPLE HAVE KNELT
APPLICATION AND NETFLIX AND
CHILL.
NETFLIX'S ORIGINAL CONTENT IS
LESS THAN 8% OF THEIR VIEWABLE
HOURS.
APPLE IS SO FAR AWAY
OPRAH TV ON APPLE TV WON'T BE
THE REASON WHY THE ECOSYSTEM
USES THEIR SERVICE SO THIS IS
GOING TO BE A DUD FOR A BID.
>>> BANK STOCKS GETTING CRUSHED.
GET A LOT WORSE FOR ONE KEY ULD
GROUP.
HE'LL BE HERE TO TELL YOU WHICH
ONE.
PLUS, TESLA IS SINKING AFTER RBC
SLASHES ITS PRICE TARGET ON THE
ELECTRIC CARMAKER.
THE STOCK JUST DID SOMETHING
THAT COULD SIGNAL A U-TURN AHEAD
AND LATER GUY IS STEPPING UP TO
THE PLATE WITH ONE STOCK HE SAYS