LYFT
>> YES
>> LET'S DO FINAL TRADES
>> DARDEN RESTAURANTS, I THINK
THAT ONE IS A GOOD ONE RIGHT
NOW, THEY'RE GOING TO CONTINUE
TO RAISE AND BEAT, IN IN THE
RESTAURANT SECTOR PER MY
ANALYST, WE'RE GOING WITH IT
>> KATE MOORE, ALWAYS GOOD TO
HAVE YOU HERE.
>> CONSUMERS, WHEN I'M WATCHING
THE MOST NEXT WEEK, I THINK
WE'RE GOING TO GET A LOT OF
DIFFERENT READS, WITH
UNEMPLOYMENT AT MULTIDECADE
LOWS, THIS IS THE BIG THING THAT
COULD CHANGE SENTIMENT
>> ALUMINA
>> TWITTER
>> MOTOROLA SOLUTIONS, MSI
>> GOOD STUFF, THANKS,
EVERYBODY.
GOOD HOLIDAY AS WELL
THE EXCHANGE STARTS NOW.
>>> D.C. AND YOUR MONEY,
POLITICIANS IN AMERICA, WILL
DEBATE THE MEANING OF THE
MUELLER REPORT, WE ASK COULD IT
LEAD TO EVEN MORE GRIDLOCK AND
STANDSTILL IN D.C.
PING AND CONFERENCING, ZOOM AND
PINTEREST HITTING THE MARKET TO
A LOT OF INVESTOR FANFARE.
COULD THEY SUFFER THE SAME
NATURE AS LYFT SHAREHOLDERS, A
FOLD FAIR, A RECYCLEABLE SHOE,
AND A NEW LEGAL SMOKING AGE.
THAT'S WHAT'S AHEAD ON RAPID
FIRE, IT'S A BIG LEAGUE SHOW
LET'S START WITH DON CHIAO
THE DOW IS UP ALMOST 100 POINT
THE.
>> AND STABLE RIGHT NOW FOR THE
MOST PART.
IF YOU TAKE A LOOK AT THE
MARKETS OVERALL, MIXED ONLY
BECAUSE THE NASDAQ IS LAGGING.
THE S&P 500 UP BY ABOUT 3 POINTS
AND THE DOW INDUSTRIALS JUST
ABOUT 100 POINTS TO THE UPSIDE,
THAT'S PRETTY DECENT OVERALL,
WE'LL SEE IF THAT STICKS, ONE
PARTICULAR INDUSTRY GROUP TO
FOCUS ON
THE I SHARES TRACKS THE DOW
TRANSPORTS, RIGHT NOW AT THE
HIGHEST LEVELS WE'VE SEEN GOING
ALL THE WAY BACK TO DECEMBER
THIRD.
SO TRANSPORT IS A BIG PART OF
THAT STORY
UNION PACIFIC EARNINGS BETTER
THAN EXPECTED.
THAT'S DRIVING THE TRADE THERE,
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR ONE OF THE
STOCKS OF THE DAY THAT'S NOT
ZOOM, THAT'S NOT PINTEREST
CHECK OUT BLACKSTONE, LOOK AT
THIS
8 1/2% GAINS, A PRIVATELY TRADED
PARTNERSHIP THAT'S GOING TO BE A
PUBLICLY TRADED CORPORATION.
A LOT MORE INVESTORS COULD COME
IN THE MIX, AND THEY RAISED A
LOT OF MONEY FOR THEIR FUNDS
LAST YEAR, BACK OVER TO YOU
MUCH.
>> SIDEWALK BOX, TALKING THAT UP
THIS MORNING
>> SO -- AND THE MARKETS THAT
DOM JUST WALKED YOU THROUGH HAVE
TWO NEW MEMBERS TO WELCOME INTO
THE FOLD TODAY
YOU'VE HEARD THE NAMES,
PINTEREST AND ZOOM ARE BOTH
PUBLIC
BOTH RISING.
JUST ADDING TO THE LIST OF
NAMES, INCLUDING SOME VERY UNDER
THE RADAR ONES THAT HAVE DONE
VERY WELL WHEN THEY HIT THE
TAPE
BOB PA SANI IS AT THE NEW YORK
STOCK EXCHANGE WITH MORE
WHAT A DAY
>> BOTH OF THEM, NOT ONLY -- THE
FLOOD GATES HAVE REALLY OPENED
NOT OWN BE DO THEY RAISE THE
TERMS GOING INTO IT, THEY POPPED
AT THE OPEN AS WELL, LET'S TAKE
A LOOK HERE, PINTEREST
PRICE TALK WAS 15 TO 17.
THEY PRICED IT AT 19
IT OPENED AT 23.75, AND TAKE A
LOOK AT IT ON INTRADAY TRADING
HERE
THEY'RE GOING TO TRADE THE WHOLE
FLOW TODAY, IT'S HOLDING UP VERY
WELL, UP 24.35
ZOOM, THOUGH, 28 TO 32, JUST
FOUR OR FIVE DAYS AGO, WE WERE
TALKING ABOUT 28 TO 32 FOR ZOOM.
PRICED AT 36, THAT'S NOT A TYPO,
IT OPENED AT $65
THIS IS VERY RARE TO SEE
SOMETHING THAT OPENS TWICE AS
HIGH AS ANYBODY THOUGHT IT WOULD
A WEEK AGO, YOU SEE IT TRADING
RIGHT HERE AT $63.
JUST OFF THAT NUMBER
IT'S PROFITABLE, A LOT OF PEOPLE
LIKE THAT, IT'S GOT 100% GROWTH,
AND THOSE ARE THE TWO MAGIC
WORDS WE GOT
RECENT IPO'S THAT JOINS A
PARADE, THEY'VE DONE REALLY
WELL
LEVI STRAUSS ALL DOING GREAT,
LYFT IS IT ONE OF THE FEW
COMPANIES STILL TO THE DOWN
SIDE, NO COMPANIES NEXT WEEK,
BRIAN, BUT THE WEEK AFTER, WE'LL
GET ANOTHER SLEW, MAYBE I HEART
MEDIA, MAYBE NEXT FRIDAY WE'LL
GET UBER GIVING US SOME TERMS,
WE'LL SEE, NOT SURE ABOUT THAT
YET.
>> BOB PA SANI, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH
>>> NOW, TO WASHINGTON
BECAUSE THE OTHER BIG THING TO
HIT THE TAPE TODAY WAS THE
MUELLER REPORT
IT'S PERHAPS MORE HEAVILY
REDACTED THAN MANY HAD THOUGHT
OR HOPED
BUT AT 400 OR SO PAGES LONG, OUR
TEAM IS STILL POURING THROUGH IT
MANY EAMON JAVERS STILL TRYING
TO DIGEST THAT
>> THE HEADLINE IS OUT THERE,
THE PRESIDENT'S BEEN SAYING THAT
THROUGHOUT THE DAY
NO COLLUSION, NO OBSTRUCTION,
THAT'S GOOD NEWS FOR THIS WHITE
HOUSE.
INSIDE THE DOCUMENT, WE'RE
FINDING SOME OF THE AREAS OF
CONCERN FOR ROBERT MUELLER,
PARTICULARLY AROUND THE AREA OF
POTENTIAL OBSTRUCTION OF THE
JUSTICE, AND THE PRESIDENT'S
PUBLIC STATEMENTS, HIS TWEETS
EVEN ABOUT SOME OF THE PEOPLE
INVOLVED IN THIS WHOLE
SITUATION, THOSE WERE RED FLAGS
FOR ROBERT MUELLER IN CERTAIN
CIRCUMSTANCES.
PARTICULARLY ON THIS IDEA OF --
>> ALL RIGHT, SO WHEN WE GET
EAMON BACK UP, SOMEONE PULLED
THE PLUG LITERALLY ON EAMON.
LET'S TALK ABOUT WHAT THIS MEANS
FOR THE MARKETS AND POLICY
GOING-FORWARD.
LET'S BRING IN LIBBY CANTRELL
HEAD OF PIMCO.
THE DEMOCRATS ARE GOING DO
COMPLAIN IT'S TOO HEAVILY
REDACTED, WE NEED TO INVESTIGATE
FURTHER.
WHAT DO YOU SEE GOING-FORWARD?
>> THIS IS HITTING THROUGH A
PARTISAN LENS.
THE REPUBLICANS ARE SORT 6
CLAIMING VINDICATION HERE, THAT
THERE'S NO COLLUSION
DEMOCRATS MAY WALK-THROUGH THE
DOOR THAT THE MUELLER REPORT
OPENED, IN TERMS OF
INVESTIGATING FURTHER, WHETHER
THERE IS OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
I THINK YOU'LL HEAR LOUDER CALLS
FOR IMPEACHMENT HEARINGS FROM
THE LEFT
SPEAKER PELOSI WILL DO
EVERYTHING SHE CAN TO NOT HEED
THOSE CALLS.
WASHINGTON IS WEATHER POLARIZED,
ALREADY PARTISAN
THERE WAS NOT LEEWAY ANYWAY.
THE BIG THINGS THAT PRESIDENT
INTERRUPT WANTS TO MOVE
LEGISLATIVELY, IS NAFTA 2.0,
THAT MIGHT BE HARDER TO MOVE NOW
WITH A MORE FRACTURED
RELATIONSHIP
>> DO YOU BELIEVE THAT, RON, TO
LIBBYS POINT THAT IN SOME WAYS
WILL AFFECT WHAT SHOULD BE
BIPARTISAN OR NONPARTISAN.
PURELY ECONOMIC NEGOTIATIONS
>> YEAH, I DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANY ESCAPING, MAYBE THE OVERHANG
THAT LIBBY ALLUDED TO.
WITHIN THE OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE COMPONENT OF THIS
REPORT
BOB MUELLER EFFECTIVELY PUNTED
TO CON AND SUGGESTED IN THE
ABSENCE OF HIS BEING ABLE TO DO
ANYTHING, WHICH SAYS YOU CANNOT
INDICT A SITTING PRESIDENT
HE REALLY SUGGESTED THAT
CONGRESS TO A CERTAIN EXTENT
TAKE THIS UP, TO THE EXTENT
THEY'RE DISTRACTED OR OBSESSED
BY THIS, IT WILL SLOW DOWN THE
LEGISLATIVE PROCESS AND CREATE
EVEN MORE FRACTURES BETWEEN THE
DEMOCRATS AND THE HOUSE, AND THE
WHITE HOUSE ITSELF
>> YOU KNOW, JOHN, WHEN BARR'S
LETTER CAME OUT, PEOPLE SAID,
OKAY, THIS IS OVER
IT APPEARS THAT RON IS
SUGGESTING MAYBE WE ARE JUST
GETTING STARTED ON A SECOND
PHASE OF THIS.
>> WELL, I THINK THAT'S BECAUSE
BARR'S LETTER WAS SUCH A BRIEF
SUMMARY OF THIS, AND THE REPORT
TODAY GIVES US A LOT MORE DETAIL
AS EAMON WAS SAYING BEFORE
SOMEBODY PULLED THE PLUG, THAT A
LOT OF DETAIL ABOUT THE
POTENTIAL OBSTRUCTION THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAD ENGAGED IN, ORDERS
TO DON McGANN THEN THE WHITE
HOUSE COUNSEL TO DIRECT ROD
ROSENSTEIN TO FIRE ROBERT
MUELLER, THE SPECIAL COUNSEL,
McGANN REFUSING, OFFERING HIS
RESIGNATION, AND ULTIMATELY
STAYING ON A WHILE LONGER AND
TELLING AIDS THAT TRUMP HAD
ASKED HIM TO DO CRAZY STUFF.
I THINK ALL OF THAT -- AND TO
LIBBY'S POINT EARLIER, I THINK
IT WAS THE RIGHT ONE
I BELIEVE THAT THE WAY THE
ADMINISTRATION THROUGH BILL BARR
IN THE LETTER, AND TODAY'S PRESS
CONFERENCE, IN WHICH HE SEEMED
TO BE SPINNING FOR THE PRESIDENT
TO BLUNT THE IMPACT OF THE
REPORT, I THINK THAT'S GOING TO
MAKE IT MORE DIFFICULT FOR
SPEAKER PELOSI TO RESIST THOSE
IN HER CAUCUS WHO INSIST ON AN
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDING TO WEIGH
THIS IN A WAY THAT THEY THINK IS
SEARCHING AND FAIR.
>> YEAH, AND EAMON JAVERS IS
ALIVE AND WELL
HE IS BACK WITH US, SOMEONE
PULLED THE PLUG BUT NOT ON HIM
LITERALLY.
>> NO CENSORSHIP HERE.
>> HE'S NOT REDACTED
YOU'VE BEEN THERE DAY IN AND DAY
OUT FOR US
YOU'VE SEEN THE BACK AND FORTH
INSIDE, THE SPEAKER'S CHAMBER
AND TALKING ABOUT THIS, WITH
SARAH SANDERS, ONE WONDERS HOW
MUCH MORE OF ANY DIALOGUE THAT
WE HAVE IS SIMPLY GOING TO BE
ABOUT THE REPORT FROM NOW ON
THE ADMINISTRATION CAN TALK
ABOUT DEFENSE SPENDING OR
INFRASTRUCTURE, OR IMMIGRATION,
WHATEVER IT IS, AND EVERY
QUESTION IS GOING TO GO BACK TO
THIS REPORT WITH THE EXCEPTION
OF MAYBE YOURS
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, THAT'S RIGHT,
I MEAN, FIRST OF ALL, THIS IS A
WHITE HOUSE THAT DOESN'T BRIEF
THE PRESS ANY MORE
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO FACE THIS
TELEADVISED SPECTACLE OF THE
WHITE HOUSE TRYING TO GET OUT
THE LINE OF THE DAY.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE THE
PRESIDENT LEAVING HERE SHORTLY
THIS AFTERNOON, IN A COUPLE
HOURS, AND REPORTERS WILL ASK
HIM QUESTIONS.
I EXPECT HE WILL TALK, HE'S BEEN
TWEETING VIGOROUSLY TODAY, HE
HAS A LOT TO SAY ABOUT THIS.
I EXPECT WE'RE GOING TO GET
LENGTHY COMMENTS FROM THE
PRESIDENT HERE
I DON'T GET THE SENSE THEY'RE
GOING TO REBUT MUCH OF THIS AT
ALL.
THEY'RE GOING TO LET THIS SIT
AND RETREAT TO THE HEADLINE OF
NO OBSTRUCTION, NO COLLUSION
AND ON THE SMALLER THINGS, LET
ALL THAT GO.
THERE'S SOME STUFF IN HERE ABOUT
SARAH SANDERS AND HOW SHE
RESPONDED TO THE COMEY FIRING BY
SUGGESTING FBI AGENTS INSIDE THE
BUREAU HAD LOST CONFIDENCE IN
COMEY AND THEY HAD HEARD FROM
COUNTLESS MEMBERS OF THE FBI WHO
SAID THEY DIDN'T LIKE COMEY, IN
HER INTERVIEW WITH THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S TEAM, SHE ADMITTED
THAT DIDN'T HAVE ANY BASIS IN
FACT AND IT WAS A SLIP OF THE
TONGUE OR SHE JUST KIND OF SAID
IT AT THE TIME, AND DIDN'T
REALLY BASE IT ON ANY FACTUAL
BASIS.
YOU KNOW, THOSE SMALLER THINGS
DOESN'T SEEM LIKE THE WHITE
HOUSE IS GOING TO ADDRESS AT
ALL, THEY MAY JUST LET THEM ALL
GO, THEY'RE CONTENT WITH THE WIN
HERE, AND THEY FEEL LIKE THEY'VE
HAD A BIG POSITIVE POLITICAL
DAY.
>> I'M NOT SURE HOW MUCH OF A
WIN THERE IS
>> I GOT THROUGH THE FIRST 50
PAGES OF THE REPORT, THERE'S
SOME MATERIALALITY WHEN IT COMES
TO WHETHER OR NOT THE CAMPAIGN
EXPECTED TO BENEFIT FROM
RUSSIA'S ACTIONS AND
INTERFERING.
NOT RISING TO THE LEVEL OF
CRIMINALITY.
BUT FROM A MARKET PERSPECTIVE,
THIS MAY -- IN MANY WAYS TURN
NEUTRAL, IN SO FAR AS WE'RE
SEEING A RESYNCHRONIZATION OF
CHINESE AND AMERICAN ECONOMIC
GROWTH, EUROPE'S THE OUTLIER AT
THE MOMENT, WE'RE SEEING THE FED
BACK OFF, AND CENTRAL BANKS
START TO STIMULATE
IF TODAY'S RETAIL SALES NUMBER
WERE ANY INDICATION OF WHERE
WE'RE GOING FROM HERE, THE
MARKET MAY RETURN THE ATTENTION
TO FUNDAMENTALS, AND MAYBE
IGNORE
>> DAMAGE YOU FOR BRING IF RIGHT
BACK DOWN THE CNBC LANE.
IT'S AMAZING THE RETAIL SALES
NUMBER BETTER THAN EXPECTED.
JOBLESS CLAIMS UNDER 200,000
GDP REVISIONS ARE GOING UP AT
GOLDMAN SACHS AND OTHERS
IT'S AMAZING THAT THIS IS
GETTING ALL THE HEADLINES, AND
IF YOU JUST FOCUSED ON THIS, YOU
WOULD THINK THIS IS THE ONLY
THING HAPPENING, OUTSIDE OF
THIS, AMERICA ROLLS ON, AND THE
ECONOMY ROLLS ON, AND THE
PRESIDENT WILL HAVE A STRONG
ECONOMY MOST LIKELY BEHIND HIM
IN THAT RE-ELECTION BID.
>> MOST LIKELY, AND OUR VIEW OF
PIMCO IS THAT WE'LL SEE 2%,
2 1/2% GROWTH HERE IN THE UNITED
STATES
YOU HAVE THE EFFECT OF FADING
FISCAL STIMULUS, AND YOU HAVE A
BIG IMPULSE FROM THE TAX BILL
THAT WAS PASSED IN LATE 2017
AND A BIG SPENDING BILL THAT WAS
PASSED IN 2018 ANOTHER AREA OF
THIS MUELLER REPORT THAT COULD
INFORM RELATIONS WITH CORNING,
THAT COULD BE RELEVANT IS THIS
IDEA OF THE FISCAL CLIFF OF
THE MARKETS ARE NOT FOCUSED ON
THIS RIGHT NOW
THAT'S BECAUSE IF COULDN'T
DOESN'T STEP IN AND KEEP
SPENDING LEVELS AT THE RATE THEY
ARE NOW, COME JANUARY 1st OF
2020, WE COULD SEE A HALF A
PERCENT HEAD WIND OF ECONOMIC
GROWTH BECAUSE OF THIS BIG
DRIVEDOWN IN SPENDING.
I THINK WE ALL UNDERSTAND THAT
CONGRESS IS EXPEDIENT.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO WANT TO DO
THAT GOING INTO --
>> THEY MAY WANT TO DO THAT.
>> JOHN HARWOOD.
>> I WANTED TO MAKE ONE POINT,
WHICH IS THAT IN TERMS OF THE
EFFECT ON THE LEGISLATIVE
AGENDA, THERE REALLY ISN'T MUCH
OF A LEGISLATIVE AGENDA, IN
THEORY, THE ADMINISTRATION WANTS
AN INFRASTRUCTURE PLAN, BUT
REPUBLICAN LEADERS IN CONGRESS
DON'T, AND THE KIND OF PLAN THE
ADMINISTRATION WANTS IS NOT WHAT
DEMOCRATS WANT
SO OTHER THAN THE USMCA WHICH IS
SIGNIFICANT, THERE ISN'T MUCH
THAT CONGRESS MIGHT DO IN THE
ABSENCE OF THIS MUELLER REPORT
I THINK THAT'S IMPORTANT AND
ALSO --
>> LET ME ASK YOU, LIBBY'S POINT
IF I CAN, WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF
TIME, DO YOU BELIEVE IT'S NOT
ONLY BECAUSE THE REPORT, BUT
MAYBE THE REPORT LAYERS ON, THAT
THE U.S. CONGRESS, DEMOCRATS AND
REPUBLICANS BOTH, WILL PLAY
ECONOMIC CHICKEN WITH THE FISCAL
CLIFF AND THE U.S. ECONOMY
>> I DOUBT IT.
I DON'T THINK, DEMOCRATS
APPROACH THESE ISSUES
DIFFERENTLY FROM REPUBLICANS,
AND WHILE THEY'LL FIGHT FOR
THEIR POLICY PRIORITIES, I DON'T
THINK THAT A NANCY PELOSI LED
HOUSE WOULD ENGAGE IN THE DEGREE
OF BRINKS MANSHIP WE'VE SEEN IN
THE PAST
>> LET'S HOPE.
535 MEN AND WOMEN FIGHTING WHILE
OTHERS MAY SUFFER.
>> EAMON JAVERS, GOOD TO SEE YOU
ARE WELL
>>> WE'RE JUST GETTING STARTED
ON THE EXCHANGE, HERE'S WHAT
ELSE IS COMING UP.
>>> AHEAD, THE CEO OF BB & T
JOINS US
WE'LL TALK EARNINGS, THE
PROGRESS ON ITS BIG MERGER AND
THE OUTLOOK FOR THE ECONOMY.
IPO BONANZA, INVESTORS PIN THEIR
HOPES ON PINTEREST
AND ZOOM
ZOOM'S HIGHER.
SHOULD YOU GET IN?
>>> AND COULD 21 SOON BE THE NEW
18 WHEN IT COMES TO TOBACCO?
WE'LL EXPLAIN.
- I love my Grandma.
- ANNCR: As you grow older,
your brain naturally
begins to change which may
cause trouble with recall.
- Learning from him is great...
when I can keep up!
- ANNCR: Thankfully,
Prevagen helps your brain
and improves memory.
- Dad's got all the answers.
- ANNCR: Prevagen is now
the number-one-selling
brain health supplement
in drug stores nationwide.
- She outsmarts me
every single time.
- Checkmate!
You wanna play again?
- ANNCR: Prevagen.
Healthier Brain. Better Life.
HNCHS SO MUCH TALK ABOUT THE
POSSIBILITY OF AN ECONOMIC
SLOWDOWN, IT'S IMPORTANT TO LOOK
YOJD THE GOVERNMENT DATA
LET'S DO MORE OF THAT BY DIVING
INTO BB & T'S LATEST QUARTER
KELLY, IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU ON
THE PROGRAM, SO MUCH DISCUSSION
ABOUT A POSSIBILITY OF A
SLOWDOWN
HOW IS BB & T SEEING LOAN
DEMAND
>> GLAD TO BE BACK
LOAN DEMAND IS ACTUALLY VERY
GOOD, ACTUALLY, PRODUCTION IS
VERY HIGH.
OUR PIPELINE WHERE WE MEASURE
ALL THE APPLICATIONS AND PROCESS
ARE AT AN ALL TIME HIGH.
AND SO WE'RE SEEING A BROAD BASE
LEVEL OF CONFIDENCE, A BROAD
BASED LEVEL OF WILLINGNESS TO
BORROW MONEY TO INVEST AND
PLANTING CAPITAL AND EQUIPMENT,
OVERALL IT'S VERY GOOD
ON THE STREET DOESN'T MATCH UP
WITH THE NATIONAL RHETORIC YOU
HEAR
>> IN YOUR EXPERIENCE, YOUR LONG
HISTORY OF RUNNING A BANK, TO
PEOPLE BORROW MONEY, DO
BUSINESSES BORROW MONEY WHEN
THEY SENSE A SLOWDOWN IS
IMMINENT
>> THEY DO, BRIAN.
IT'S INTERESTING
>> THEY DO
>> YEAH, THEY DO
I TRAVEL AROUND AND TALK TO LOTS
OF BUSINESS PEOPLE, ONE ON ONE,
AND SO WHEN I TALK TO THEM, THEY
TALK ABOUT THEIR BUSINESS.
THEY'RE CHATTING ABOUT THE
NATIONAL ISSUES.
WHEN YOU GET RIGHT DOWN TO WHAT
THEY'RE GOING TO DO, THEY FOCUS
ON THEIR BUSINESS.
SO IF THEIR ACTUAL MARKET IS
SLOWING DOWN, THEY WILL REDUCE
THEIR INVESTMENT
BUT IF IT'S JUST A LOT OF -- A
GENERAL CONVERSATION, THEY'LL
TALK ABOUT IT.
MIGHT CAUSE THEM EASINESS.
THEY'LL FOCUS ON RUNNING THEIR
BUSINESS
>> FORRAL THE NUMBERS, THE
QUARTER AND THE YEAR SO FAR, DO
YOU BELIEVE WE WILL BE IN A
RECESSION IN 12 TO 18 MONTHS
>> YOU KNOW, I ACTUALLY DO NOT
I'LL BE HONEST, 6 OR 8, 9 MONTHS
AGO, I WAS A LITTLE MORE
CONCERNED ABOUT THE POSSIBILITY
OF THAT.
THERE WAS SO MUCH RHETORIC ABOUT
TEN YEARS, AFTER A WHILE,
EVERYBODY BEGINS TO HAVE THAT
EFFECT
BUT AS I'VE GOTTEN AROUND AND
TALKED TO BUSINESS PEOPLE, AS I
SEE THE STRENGTH, JUST WHAT
YOU'VE BEEN REPORTING IN THE
LAST HOUR OR SO.
STRONG RETAIL SALES, LOW
UNEMPLOYMENT, LOW JOBLESS
CLAIMS, NO MAJOR GEO POLITICAL
RISK THAT SEEMS TO BE EMINENTLY
PROBLEMATIC, I DON'T SEE -- AND
CERTAINLY IN THOSE 12 TO 18
MONTHS, I DO NOT SEE AN IMMINENT
SLOWDOWN, I THINK THAT YOU COULD
HAVE SOME EXISTENTIAL FACTORS
THAT COULD CAUSE THAT I DON'T
THINK IT'S PREDICTABLE AT THIS
HAD TIME
>> ONE THING THAT STOOD OUT TO
ME, IT WAS A LITTLE SHOCKING, I
GUESS, YOUR NET INTEREST MARGIN
ROSE ONLY TWO BIPS
LITERALLY.
A TINY PERCENT
>> WE'LL TAKE WHAT WE CAN GET.
>> IT ROSE EVEN AS INTEREST RATE
S LOWERED.
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
>> REAR A REALLY BIG COMMUNITY
BANK, WE OPERATE OUR REGIONAL
BANK STRUCTURE, WE'RE IN A LOT
OF RURAL AREAS, METRO URBAN
AREAS AS WELL.
WE HAVE A LOT OF STABLE
DEPOSITS, THEY'RE MORE FOCUSED
ON RELATIONSHIPS, A LOT OF SMALL
BUSINESS CLIENTS
AND SO IT -- OUR NIM PRESSURE IS
MORE A FUNCTION OF WHAT'S
HAPPENING IN OUR LOCAL MARKETS
THAN IT IS IN THE NATIONAL
MARKETS.
WHEN YOU HEAR A LOT OF NATIONAL
DISCUSSION ABOUT CHANGES IN NIM,
IT DOESN'T INHERENTLY AFFECT US.
IF WE DO SOME EXTERNAL LARGE
FUNDING, THAT WILL MOVE OUR NIM
AROUND A LITTLE BIT, BUT IN THIS
PARTICULAR QUARTER, WHAT WE
REALLY SAW WAS THAT OUR FUNDING
WAS INCREASING, BUT OUR RATE OF
RETURN ON ASSETS WAS INCREASING
AT A FASTER RATE
>> YOU KNOW, ONE QUICK LAST
QUESTION
YOU'RE PAYING AN ADVERTISING
AGENCY A LOT OF MONEY TO COME UP
WITH A NEW BRAND BETWEEN SUN
TRUST AND BB & T WHEN YOU MERGE.
CAN YOU GIVE US A HINT AS TO
WHAT THAT'S SHAPING UP TO BE,
SUN TRUST AND BB & T COULD MORE
TOGETHER LIKE A KIDS DRINK IF
YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL
>> THE REASON WE DECIDED TO PICK
A NEW NAME VERSUS USING EITHER
ONE OF THE OTHERS, OUR MERGER IS
ABOUT IMPROVING PROFITABILITY
WHICH IT DOES ENORMOUSLY
IT'S ABOUT LINING FORWARD, MAJOR
INVESTMENTS AND INNOVATION,
TECHNOLOGY, IT'S ABOUT GETTING
EXCITING ABOUT MEETING THE NEEDS
OF THE CLIENTS IN TERMS OF
TECHNOLOGY AND TRUST, KIND OF
THAT RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN
TECHNOLOGY AND BRANCHS
AND SO WE WANT TO NAME THE
POINTS FORWARD THAT EXCITES OUR
CLIENTS, OUR ASSOCIATES AND THE
MARKET IN GENERAL TO SAY THIS IS
AN INSTITUTION THAT IS MOVING
FORWARD, IS ENERGIZED AND TRYING
TO TAKE CARE OF THE COMMUNITY AT
LARGE AND CLIENTS IN PARTICULAR,
WE THINK WE CAN FIND SUCH A
NAME
>> GOOD LUCK, WE DO WISH YOU
LUCK
APPRECIATE THAT, HAVE A GOOD
EASTER
THANK YOU.
>>> ON DECK, THE TRADE WAR COMES
HOME, HOW CHINA AND WISCONSIN
ARE NOW IN A FIGHT AND IT'S OVER
WHAT SOME SAYS FOXCONN'S BROKEN
PROMISES
FIRST, TO THE MOON, ZOOM BOTH
STOCKS TRADING, DO WE NEED TO
LEARN FROM LYFT THAT ONE DAY
DOES NOT AN INVESTMENT MAKE?
Who says our bank
isn't tech enough?
Everyone, look
at your phones.
The design thinking,
the digital engineering,
security, blockchain,
and we will be first to market!
Yes.
When we do we launch?
Unfortunately, in 2 or 3,
hours.
Why the delay?
Cognizant is helping
banks use digital technologies
at scale to
advance speed to market.
>>> PINTEREST AND ZOOM MAY BE
GETTING ALL THE HEAD LINING LOVE
TODAY.
THEY'RE NOT THE ONLY NAMES YOU
NEED TO WORRY ABOUT ABOUT SECOND
QUARTER PROFIT GUIDANCE BELOW
FORECAST
THAT STOCK IS DOWN
HONEY WELL IS UP, THEY POSTED
STRONG RESULTS AND RAISED THEIR
FULL YEAR FORECAST
THE COMPANY SAYING IT'S ALL
STRONG DEMAND FOR ITS AEROSPACE
PRODUCTS
AND TRAVELERS TAKING A JOURNEY
HIGHER TODAY, LEADING THE DOW.
DIVIDEND AND NET STOCK IS
HIGHER
>>> LET'S GET TO CORN TESSA
BREWER
>> DEMOCRATS VYING FOR THE PARTY
IN THE 2020 PRESIDENTIAL
NOMINATION, INCLUDING KIRSTEN
GILLIBRAND
SHE HAD SOME HARSH WORDS ABOUT
BARR'S NEWS CONFERENCE THIS
MORNING.
>> THE ATTORNEY GENERAL OF THE
UNITED STATES IS SUPPOSED TO
REPRESENT THE PEOPLE OF THE
UNITED STATES, HE'S NOT SUPPOSED
TO REPRESENT PRESIDENT TRUMP BY
HAVING THIS PRESS CONFERENCE
TODAY, MISLEADING THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE WAS NOT APPROPRIATE
>>> INVESTIGATORS THINK AN
ELECTRICAL SHORT CIRCUIT MOST
LIKELY CAUSED NOTRE DAME'S
CATHEDRAL FIRE
THE INVESTIGATORS DON'T HAVE THE
GREEN LIGHT TO WORK IN THE
CATHEDRAL BECAUSE OF SAFETY
CONCERNS
>> RESCUE SERVICES USE TWO
CRANES TO PULL OUT A BUS
KILLED 29 AND INJURED 28 PEOPLE.
THE BUS WAS LYING ON ITS SIDE
WITH PART OF ITS ROOF TORN OFF
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH
>>> A PAIR OF TECHNOLOGY
UNICORNS, MILLION DOLLARS IN THE
PUBLIC MARKET ARE SURGING AFTER
THEIR PUBLIC DEBUTS TODAY.
PINTEREST BRYCING ABOVE THE HIGH
END OF THE RANGE OF $19 A SHARE.
OPENED UP 25%.
THAT SOUNDS GOOD, UNTIL YOU HEAR
THIS
ZOOM VIDEO COMMUNICATIONS,
PRICED AT $36 A SHARE.
ONLY OPENED UP 80%
LET'S TALK ABOUT BOTH, START
WITH BEN SILVERMAN CALLING
SIDEWALK ALLY, THE COMPANY IS
MORE ABOUT UTILITY FOR PEOPLE TO
GET THINGS DONE AND LESS OF A
PLACE TO TALK FOR FRIENDS OR TO
FOLLOW CELEBRITIES
WE ARE NOT A SOCIAL MEDIA
COMPANY.
FOR MORE, LET'S BRING IN
DIRECTING MANAGER OF LOOP
VENTURES
AMAZING RESPONSE TO PINTEREST.
ARE YOU SURPRISED?
A 25% POP?
EITHER THE BANKERS SCREWED UP IN
PRICING IT OR PEOPLE REALLY LIKE
PINTEREST.
>> IT'S A DISCOVERY PLATFORM,
IT'S NOT A SOCIAL NETWORK.
WE THINK IT WILL BE COMPED LIKE
A SOCIAL NETWORK
THE GOOD THING ABOUT PINTEREST
IS, IT'S A GREAT BUSINESS.
PEOPLE TELL PINTEREST HOW THEY
SEE THE WORLD IN PICTURES.
FACEBOOK AND TWITTER ARE TRADING
6 TO 8 TIMES NEXT YEAR'S RE
REVENUE.
IT FEELS LIKE THE MARKET IS
PRICING IN A LOT OF THAT --
>> FIRST OF ALL, I THINK THE
TERM SOCIAL MEDIA IS OUTDATED
AND DONE
DO YOU THINK THERE WAS A
STRATEGIC REASON WHY THE CEO OF
PINTEREST KEPT SAYING, WE'RE NOT
SOCIAL MEDIA
YOU WANT THAT STAIN?
>> YEAH, I THINK SOCIAL MEDIA'S
A BAD WORD RIGHT NOW
>> TWO WORDS
>> TWO BAD WORDS
COMBINED INTO ONE.
I THINK YOU LOOK AT FACEBOOK AND
TWITTER AND WHAT'S HAPPENED WITH
THEM, PUBLIC SENTIMENT AROUND --
ESPECIALLY PRIVACY ON FACEBOOK,
BUT THE CONVERSATION
POLITICALLY.
THE DISCOURSE IS DIFFICULT ON
BOTH PLOOT FORMS, PINTEREST
TALKS A LOT ABOUT EMPOWERING
THEIR USERS, IT'S A DIFFERENT
MESSAGE THAN WHAT WE'RE SEEING
FACEBOOK AND TWITTER DOING WITH
THEIR USERS, WHERE YOU HAVE FOMO
AND DEPRESSION
>> BESIDES YOU, YOU KNOW WHAT'S
AMAZING, IF A STOCK FALLS 25%,
EVERYONE SCREAMS, WALL STREET
REALLY SCREWED THAT UP
IF A STOCK RISES 25%
NOBODY'S SAYING ANYTHING, IT'S
STILL OBVIOUSLY 25% MISPRICED,
YOU SEE WHERE I'M GOING WITH
THIS
>> YEAH, IT'S TOUGH TO PRICE AN
IPO PERFECTLY, IF IT CLOSED FLAT
TODAY, PEOPLE WOULD COMPLAIN
ABOUT THAT TOO
IN TERMS OF PINTEREST, THIS
COMPANY SOLD PRIMARY SHARES
ONLY, WHICH MEANS THAT ALL OF
THE MONEY RAISED FROM THE IPO
WENT BACK INTO THE COFFERS OF
THE COMPANY, THERE WERE NO
SELLING SHAREHOLDERS THAT WERE
RAISING MONEY TO FUND THEIR OWN
POCKETS.
WHAT THAT MEANS ESSENTIALLY IF
YOU SEE A 25% POP, THAT IS A
LOSS OF CAPITAL, THAT IS MONEY
LEFT ON THE TABLE THAT PINTEREST
COULD HAVE OTHERWISE USE TO
REINVEST IN THEIR BUSINESS
THAT SAID, IS IMPORTANT TO KEEP
INVESTORS HAPPY.
YOU WANT INVESTORS THAT ARE
GOING TO STICK AROUND FOR THE
LONG RUN, THROUGH THAT SIX MONTH
LOCKUP PERIOD WHICH EXPIRES IN
ABOUT 180 DAYS, YOU WANT PEOPLE
THAT CAN STICK AROUND, AND THE
BEST WAY TO MAKE THEM HAPPY IS
TO MAKE THEM MONEY, BRIAN.
>> IT CERTAINLY IS
>> LET'S MOVE ON TO ZOOM VIDEO
IF YOU THOUGHT PINTEREST IS
DOING WELL
ZOOM, NEW TICKER ZM, SOARING UP
MORE THAN 75%.
ZOOM GETTING A LOT OF LOVE, BUT
IT ALSO FACES A LOT OF
COMPETITION P.M.
>> ZOOCHM'S PERFORMANCE SAYS A T
ABOUT OTHER TECH NAMES THAT
HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO GAIN ON
THIS VIDEO CONFERENCING.
ZOOM COMES OUT OF NOWHERE AND
TAKES THIS FIELD AND IS THE
LEADER AND KNOWN TO BE EASIER TO
USE, AND PART OF THE REASON FOR
THAT IS BECAUSE IT STARTED IN
THE CLOUD.
SOME OF THE OTHER COMPETITORS
AND BIG NAMES IN THIS SPACE
STARTED ON ANTEQUATEZ CONFERENCE
CALL
HOW CAN IT CONTINUE TO COMPETE
AGAINST THESE CAPITALIZED BIG
TECH NAME COMPETITORS.
THEY'VE BUILT A COMPANY THAT WAS
MORE SIMPLE AND EASIER TO USE.
YOU CAN UNDERSTAND HOW IT MAY BE
CONTINUING TO USE THIS STRENGTH?
>> DEIRDRE BOSA, GREAT
DISCUSSION, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> HERE'S WHAT'S AHEAD ON THE
EXCHANGE
>> COMING UP, CANNABIS
CONSOLIDATION HEATS UP
COULD BIG CHANGES BE COMING TO
THE TOBACCO WORLD?
>>> PLUS, A RECYCLEABLE SNEAKER.
AND A FOLD FAIR, THAT'S ALL
AHEAD IN RAPID FIRE.
We see homes staying cooler
without the planet
getting warmer.
At Emerson,
when issues become inspiration,
creating a better world
isn't just a result,
it's a responsibility.
Emerson.
Consider It Solved.
>>> LET'S CATCH YOU UP ON A FEW
STORIES THAT SHOULD BE ON YOUR
RADAR RIGHT NOW.
RAPID FIRE, WE HAVE BILL
GRIFFITH, KATE ROGERS, FRANK
COLIN, ONLY ONE OF U.S. WILL
EMERGE ALIVE
>> ARE WE GOING TO GET A WORD IN
EDGEWISE HERE, MY FRIEND
>> I WANT TO SURVIVE
>> YOU WIN
MITCH McCONNELL ANNOUNCING A
BILL THAT WILL PUMP THE NATIONAL
MINIMUM AGE FROM 18 TO 21.
IT'S A BILL, NOT A LAW YET
IT WOULD ALSO APPLY TO VAPPING
PRODUCTS
WE SHOULD KNOW, SOME STATES IN
AMERICA HAVE A MINIMUM AGE OF
THIS WOULD BE A SYMBOLIC MOVE.
IT'S YOUR BEAT HERE, WHAT'S THE
REACTION
WHAT DO YOU THINK.
>> HERE'S THE THING, A LOT OF
STATS WE CAN THROW OUT HERE,
HERE'S ANOTHER ONE
90% OF CURRENT SMOKERS TRIED A
CIGARETTE BY THE TIME THEY WERE
THERE ARE 16 MILLION AMERICANS
WITH A SMOKING DISEASE IN
AMERICA RIGHT NOW.
>> THIS IS THE TOBACCO INDUSTRY
TRYING TO GET AHEAD OF
RESTRICTIONS THAT MAY COME OUT
WHY NOW?
THERE WAS A 75% INCREASE IN THE
USE OF VAPPING BY TEENS.
SURPRISE, SURPRISE, THE TOBACCO
COMPANIES ARE SUPPORTING SAID
LEGISLATION TO RAISE THE MINIMUM
AGE FOR SMOKING TO 21.
>> JUUL IS IN SUPPORT OF 21
YEARS OLD TO BUY TOBACCO ABOUT
THE McCONNELL RELEASE DID HAVE
SOME DISTURBING ITEMS, INCLUDING
MIDDLE SCHOOLERS ARE STARTING TO
VAP.
I TOTALLY AGREE WITH THE MARKET,
IT SEEMS LIKE CANDY AND YOU
DON'T REALIZE THERE'S NICOTINE
IN IT, IT'S NOT GOOD FOR YOU
>> THERE'S MONTH NICOTINE IN IT,
THAN IN REGULAR CIGARETTES
>> SO IT'S TIME TO GO TO 21
ANYWAY, THEY SHOULD HAVE DONE
THAT YEARS AGO
THE DRINKING AGE IS 21
>> A LOT OF STATES AND TOWNS
HAVE ALREADY RAISED IT
TWO THINGS CAN BE RIGHT AT THE
SAME TIME.
IT'S ALSO GOOD FOR PUBLIC.
>> YOU ARE THE YOUNGEST ONE ON
THIS PANEL
DO YOU BELIEVE RAISING THE
AGE --
>> I'M NOT ASKING YOU TO REVEAL
ANY PERSONAL DETAILS ABOUT HIGH
SCHOOL
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT RAISING THE
AGE OF SOMETHING DOES PREVENT
PEOPLE FROM DOING IT
>> I WAS AN ANGEL IN HIGH
SCHOOL, I AM STILL TODAY
>> I THINK IF KIDS WANT TO GET
THEIR HANDS ON SOMETHING, WE CAN
PREVENT IT BY PUTTING LAWS LIKE
THIS IN PLACE, LIKE I SAID, WHEN
S THAT --
>> SELLING JUUL PODS AT THE HIGH
SCHOOL
>>> CANNABIS CONSOLE DAGS,
STRIKING A $4.3 BILLION DEAL TO
BUY ACREAGE HOLDING.
THAT DEAL WILL TAKE EFFECT
AFRICAN IN A BUS HAS BEEN
LEGALIZED IN THE U.S., WHILE
LEGAL CANNABIS SALES HAVE BEEN
CLIMBING THIS YEAR, SO FAR, THE
BLACK MARKETS HAVE BEEN RISING,
WHAT'S THE FUTURE BILL OF THIS
INDUSTRY
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I FIND
INTERESTING, THIS IS A FUTURE'S
CONTRACT FOR CANOPY.
LOCKING IN A PRICE
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, I WONDER
WHY ACREAGE WOULD DO THIS DEAL
IF THEY'RE LOCKING THEMSELVES
INTO -- IT'S A 43% PREMIUM OVER
THE COMPANY'S VALUATION RIGHT
NOW, WHAT'S TO SAY THEY COULDN'T
SEE AN EVEN HIGHER VALUATION,
AFTER WE DO INEVITABLY SEE --
>> YOU'RE SAYING THIS COULD BE A
SIGN OF LACK OF OPTIMISM
>> CANOPY IS MAKING A SMART
PLAY
>> ACREAGE IS A MULTISTATE
OPERATOR
THIS IS CONTINGENT ON FEDERAL
LEGALIZATION, BUT REALLY SMART
MOVE FOR CANOPY AND
CONSTELLATION, WHICH I KNOW YOU
HAVE YOUR EYE ON
>> YEAH.
THEY HAVE SOME WARRANTS WHERE
THEY CAN -- SIMILAR OPTION, THEY
CAN DECIDE TO BUY MORE STAKE IN
CANOPY
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE TALKING
ABOUT THE CANNABIS PLAY.
I'M LOOKING AT THE ACREAGE
BUSINESS
THEY HAVE BILL WELD, A GUY
RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT.
I FEEL LIKE CANOPY MAY BE BUYING
THAT INFLUENCE
LET'S GET DOWN TO BUSINESS
WEED'S A COMMODITY, EVERYBODY'S
GOING TO BE ABLE TO GROW IT.
>> AND JOHN BOEHNER --
>> SO I'VE BEEN TOLD
>>> UP NEXT, LET'S TALK ABOUT
RECYCLEABLE SHOWS.
>> SHE TOLD ME
>> HE TOLD ME.
I HEARD IT FROM YOU.
>> HE MIGHT HAVE
ADIDAS JUST RELEASED A NEW
RUNNING SHOE MADE FROM 100%
RECYCLEABLE MATERIAL, ONCE YOUR
SHOES HAVE FALLEN APART, YOU CAN
RETURN THEM TO AIDID AS WHERE
THEY RECYCLE FOR THE COMPONENT
TO MAKE A NEW PAIR OF KICKS ZION
WILLIAMSON SHOULD BE THEIR
SPOKESPERSON
>> I WAS THINKING.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK, GIMMICK OR
REAL --
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE ADIDAS WANTS
TO GIVE THIS RIGHT
THEY'RE GIVING IT TO 200 RUNNERS
TO TEST THEM OUT
THEY WANT TO MAKE SURE --
>> THEY WANT TO MAKE SURE THEY
REALLY GET THIS RIGHT.
>> HOW LONG DO THEY LAST
>> I THINK CONSUMERS CARE MORE
AND MORE BEFORE THIS, MORE
COMPANIES ARE PAYING ATTENTION
TO ECOFRIENDLY
MARKETING THINGS IN THIS WAY
YOU.
>> KNOW WHAT THEY CARE ABOUT
MORE, NOT ROLLING THEIR ANKLE OR
HAVING THEIR KNEES HURT WHEN
THEY JOG
>> RECYCLING IS BECOMING A BIG
BUSINESS RIGHT NOW
AND AS WE ALL KNOW, JASON MOMOA
JUST SHAVED HIS BEARD FOR THE
OBVIOUS REASON THAT HE'S
PROMOTING ALUMINUM AS A
RECYCLING THING.
>> STOP THE APPRECIATIONS.
>> HERE'S THE THING, DON'T COME
AT THIS AS A BUSINESS
JOURNALIST
YOU'RE A 6'5" INCH DUDE, I DON'T
KNOW IF YOU RUN.
LISTEN, WE RUN, IT HURTS
THE SHOES GOT TO WORK, FIRST AND
FOREMOST
>> ZION WILLIAMSON WAS A PERFECT
EXAMPLE, IF THE SHOE CAN'T HOLD
UP, IT'S A PROBLEM
IT THIS IS REALLY
DIFFERENTIATION.
ADIDAS HAS BEEN TRYING TO
INCREASE ITS MARKET SHARE.
THEY SIGNED KANYE TO A SNEAKER
DEAL, HE'S NOT REALLY RUNNING
ANYWHERE
>> BUT THOSE SNEAKERS ARE SO
COOL
THEY DON'T NEED TO RUN ANYWHERE.
>> YOU RAN THE MARATHON?
>> FINALLY, WE'RE MOVING ON.
REMEMBER HOW MUCH HYPE SAMSUNG'S
FOLDABLE PHONE GENERATED
IT'S GOT A $2,000 PRICE TAG.
SOME REVIEWERS WHO GOT THIS
PHONE EARLY, REPORTED IT BROKE
TODD HALE FOUND THE SCREEN WAS
FLICKERING AFTER JUST TWO DAYS
SAMSUNG, A REAL PROBLEM?
OR THEY JUST HAVEN'T FIGURED IT
OUTIEST.
>> I THINK IT'S A BIGGER PROBLEM
RIGHT NOW.
NOVELTY IS A BIG SALES ITEM FOR
TECHNOLOGY
THIS WAS NOVEL TO HAVE THE
FOLDING PHONE.
BUT I THINK THEY'RE GETTING
AHEAD OF THEMSELVES NOW, THEY'RE
RUSHING PRODUCTS TO MARKET
BEFORE THEY'RE READY AND THEY
COST TOO MUCH NOW BY THE WAY,
$1980 FOR A FOLDABLE PHONE IS
BECOMING TOO COMPLICATED AND TOO
EXPENSIVE.
>> CALL ME OLD FASHION, BUT I
DON'T NEED MY PHONE TO FOLD IN
HALF, I NEED IT TO HAVE A NICE
CAMERA, GOOD RECEPTION AND KIND
OF LOOK COOL
I DON'T CARE THAT MUCH
I WOULDN'T BUY THIS, I'M NOT WHO
THEY'RE MARKETING TO
>> WOMEN AND MEN, WE KEEP OUR
PHONE HERE OR IN OUR JEANS
POCKET
HAVING A PHONE THAT CAN FLEX A
LITTLE BIT WHEN YOU'RE A GUY
HELPS OUT FRANKLY, DOES IT NOT
>> BUT THE PHONE ISN'T FLEXIBLE.
>> BUT YOU COULD PUT IT HERE IN
THIS POCKET A LITTLE EASIER.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT, I
TALKED TO TODD ABOUT THIS A
LITTLE DEEPER, HE SAYS THE
RESOLUTION ON THE SCREEN ISN'T
AS GOOD AND THE COLORS AREN'T AS
GOOD
IF YOUR WHOLE SELLING POINT IS
THAT THE SCENE IS BETTER
>> SOME OF THE VIEWERS
ACCIDENTALLY, THEY TOOK IT OFF
THINKING --
>> HE DID NOT DO THAT.
>> SOME PEOPLE DID, BUT IT'S NOT
A REMOVABLE SCREEN
THEY PEELED THE SCREEN OFF
>> HE TWEETED UP CLOSE PHOTOS
THAT HE DID NOT DO THAT AND HIS
SCREEN STILL WAS FLICKERING.
>> KATE ROGERS, YES OR NO,
$2,000 PHONE
>> NO, NOT FOR ME.
BUT YOU NEED TO GET IT RIGHT, WE
TALKED ABOUT APPLE'S WIRELESS
CHARGING MAT THAT THEY PULLED
FROM THE MARKET BECAUSE THEY
SAID IT WASN'T READY
>> WHERE'S THE BUTTON, I PRESS A
BUTTON AND YOU AND YOU FALL INTO
THE ALLIGATOR PITS
>> AND I SURVIVE
>> YOU SURVIVE
>> ALL I CAN SAY IS, I'M
EXHAUSTED NOW.
>> COME ON TRENDING STORIES WITH
BILL GRIFFITH ONE MORNING.
>> OKAY, I WILL.
>>> FOXCONN FAILS TO DELIVER ON
JOBS IN SCSIHAWIONN, WT THE
GOVERNOR PLANS TO DO ABOUT THAT
NEXT
looked at chart patterns.
I've even built my own
historic trading model.
And you're still not sure if you
want to make the trade?
Exactly.
Sounds like a case of
analysis paralysis.
Is there a cure?
TD Ameritrade's trade desk.
They can help gut check
your strategies
and answer all your
toughest questions.
Sounds perfect.
See, your stress level was here
and I got you down to here,
I've done my job.
Call for a Strategy Gut Check
with TD Ameritrade.
♪♪
>>> FOXCONN BACK IN FOCUS TODAY
WITH ITS WISCONSIN JOBS PLEDGE
BEING CALLED INTO QUESTION
HE WANTS TO RENEGOTIATE THE
DEAL, SAYING THE COMPANY WILL
NOT BE CREATING THE 13,000 JOBS
THAT IT PLEDGED.
FOR MORE ON THIS BIG STORY,
LET'S BRING IN ONE OF THE
REPORTERS NOLLING THAT STORY
FROM THE BEGINNING
RICK, THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR
JOINING US, CNBC WAS THERE, WE
WERE IN KENOSHA AS WELL, A LOT
OF PROMISE
WHAT APPEARS TO BE FALLING
THROUGH THE CRACKS HERE?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, WE'RE ALL
SORT OF WAITING TO SEE WHETHER
FOXCONN WILL COME THROUGH ON
WHAT IT HAS SAID IT WILL DO, AND
I THINK IT'S FAIR TO SAY THAT
THE PROGRESS TOWARD THOSE GOALS
HAS BEEN SLOW.
>> HOW SLOW, AS IN SLOW, WE'RE
GETTING THERE EVENTUALLY, OR
SLOW AS IN THE CAR IS NOT MOVING
DOWN THE HIGHWAY
>> THE CAR IS MOVING, IT MIGHT
BE MOVING AT 25 MILES AN HOUR OR
SOMETHING.
THEY'VE MADE MULTIPLE CHANGES TO
THEIR PLANS FOR THIS PLANT
INITIALLY THEY SAID IT WAS GOING
TO BE A GENERATION 10.5 FLAT
SCREEN PLANT
WHICH IS THE LARGEST MOST
EXPENSIVE TYPE OF PLANT IN THIS
INDUSTRY
FINALLY, MIDDLE OF LAST YEAR,
THEY ACKNOWLEDGED, NO WE'RE NOT
GOING TO BUILD A GENERATION 10
PLANT, IT'S GOING TO BE A
GENERATION SIX PLANT
SMALLER, LESS COSTLY, A MONTH OR
TWO AGO, IT LOOKED LIKE THEY
WERE THINKING ABOUT BACKING AWAY
FROM BUILDING A FACTORY AT ALL
IN WISCONSIN, THEN THE PRESIDENT
DONALD TRUMP GETS ON THE PHONE
TO CHAIRMAN OF FOXCONN
ALL OF A SUDDEN WITHIN HOURS,
THEY COME OUT WITH A STATEMENT
SAYING, YES, WE WILL BUILD THIS
SMALLER TYPE OF FACTORY.
FOXCONN CONTINUES TO MAINTAIN IT
WILL CREATE 13,000 JOBS, A LOT
OF PEOPLE IN WISCONSIN JUST
DON'T.
THEY'RE NOT BUYING THAT.
>> DO YOU BELIEVE.
DO YOUR NEIGHBORS BELIEVE THAT
THIS PLANT WILL EVER GET BUILT
>> I -- PERSONALLY, YEAH
I THINK THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
THAT SOMETHING IS GOING TO BE
BUILT THERE, I MEAN, THEY
ALREADY ARE -- THEY HAVE
CONSTRUCTION UNDERWAY, SO
THEY'VE PREPARED A VERY LARGE
LIKE -- I DON'T KNOW, IT MIGHT
BE 60 ACRE SITE THAT HAS GRAVEL
COMPRESSED DOWN TIGHT TO BE THE
BED FOR THE FOUNDATION OF THE
PLANT.
THEY LET CONTRACTS ABOUT 2, 3
WEEKS AGO, FOR $34 MILLION WORTH
OF THE ACTUAL BUILDING
CONSTRUCTION
AND THAT'S -- THAT PART IS
UNDERWAY, AS FAR AS I CAN TELL,
AND THEY SAY THAT THIS SUMMER,
THEY WILL START BUILDING ACTUAL
PHYSICAL VERTICAL CONSTRUCTION
ITSELF
>> WHEN THEY DO THAT, YOU LET US
KNOW, YOU TAKE PICTURES WE'LL
GET YOU BACK ON CNBC
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> YOU BET, THANK YOU, BRIAN
>> COMING UP, THE SEARS DRAMA,
YOU THOUGHT IT WAS OVER, IT'S
NOT.
THE COMPANY IS SUING FORMER CEO
EDDIE LAMB PERT AND OTHERS.
CLUDING STEVEN MNUCHIN
SEARS VERSUS STEVEN, NEXT.
globa,
the rhythm of the world.
But to us,
it's the pace of tomorrow.
With ingenuity,
technologies,
and markets expertise
we create the possible.
And when you do that,
you don't chase
the pace of tomorrow.
You set it.
NASDAQ. REWRITE TOMORROW.
>>> JUST WHEN YOU THOUGHT IT WAS
OVER, THE SEARS DRAMA IS
RESURFACING.
THE COMPANY IS NOW SUES EDDIE
LAMPER FOR ALLEGEDLY STEALS
BILLIONS FROM THE CORPORATION.
THE LAWSUIT ALLEGES THAT LAMPER
ALONG WITH SEARS' BIGGEST
SHAREHOLDERS UNDULY BENEFITED
FROM DEALS THAT OCCURRED UNDER
HIS WATCH.
THE SUIT NAMES OTHER DEFENDANTS
AS WELL.
BESIDE LAMPER THEY INCLUSIVE
STEPHEN MNUCHIN AND BRUCE
BERKOWITZ.
SEARS HOLDINGS FILED FOR
BANKRUPTCY THIS PAST OCTOBER.
>>> COMING UP, ONLY ONE THIRD OF
THE UNITED STATES REQUIRED
STUDENTS TO GRADUATE WITH A
PERSON FINANCE CLASS, JUST ONE
CLASS.
THAT'S A BIG PROBLEM, SHE'S JOIL
US AND TALK ABOUT WHAT HER GROUP
IS DOING ABOUT THAT, NEXT.
and unrivaled network to work.
The United States Postal
Service makes more
e-commerce deliveries
to homes
than anyone else
in the country.
SFX: [phone ringing]
e-commerce deliveries
to homes
You still have service?
Call the Insurance company
It's them, calling us.
It's going to be a week
before they can get
through on these roads
Shhh, sorry,
I didn't catch that.
I said ask how
soon they can be here
Not you.
Right now?
What's now?
He says they're
surveying our property now
They're probably
at the wrong house
I don't see any hovering
His name is hovering?
Look up?
By using machine learning and
analytics to automate claims,
Cognizant is helping
insurance companies advance
how they serve even
the hardest-to-reach
customers.
Cool
♪♪
Every year, our analysts
visit thousands of companies,
in a multitude of countries,
where we get to know the people
that drive a company's growth
and gain new perspectives.
That's why we go
beyond the numbers.
T. Rowe Price.
Invest with Confidence.
>>> JOINS US NOTICE IS THE
AUTHOR OF THAT PIECE, NAN
MORRISON, THE COUNCIL FOR
ECONOMIC EDUCATION, ALSO A
MEMBER OF OUR WELLNESS COUNCIL
IT'S AMAZING, NAN, YOU CAN BE IN
HIGH SCHOOL AND TAKE CLASSES ON
THE PELOPONESIAN WAR, BUT NOT
FINANCES
>> EXACTLY
WE DON'T DO A GOOD JOB OF
GETTING FINANCIAL EDUCATION IN
OUR K THROUGH 12 SCHOOLS
THAT'S THE MISSION OF OUR
ORGANIZATION, TO DO THAT, TO
TEACH KIDS ABOUT PERSONAL
FINANCE AND ECONOMICS SO THEY
CAN MAKE BETTER DECISION, SO
THEY KNOW HOW TO MANAGE MONEY,
TO MAKE GOOD DECISIONS ABOUT A
CREDIT CARD OR LOANS
WITHOUT GETTING INTO THE
POL
POLITICS, IT'S HARD TO GET NEW
CLASSES CREATED.
WHAT'S THE BEST WAY TO DO THAT
WHAT'S BEEN THE HOLDUP FOR
SAYING, HEY, YOU DON'T NEED THAT
14th HISTORY CLASS, LET'S TALK
ABOUT NOT GOING BANKRUPT.
>> WE TELL TEACHERS, HELP THEM
WITH ET CONTENT, GIVE THEM
LESSONS AND HOW TO INTEGRATE IT
INTO THE EVERYDAY LIFE
SO THINK ABOUT INTEGRATING IT
INTO MATH.
INSTEAD OF THOSE CRAZY PROBLEMS
ABOUT THE AM TRACK TRAINS, HOW
MANY TIMES HAVE YOU THOUGHT
ABOUT HOW FAST THAT OTHER TRAIN
IS COMING AT YOU, BUT NO, YOU
THINK ABOUT WHAT YOUR
INVESTMENTS ARE DOING?
WE SHOULD BE TEACHING THOSE
EXAMPLES IN MATH.
>> THE WEIRD THING ABOUT THIS
AREA IS YOU HAVE LITERALLY WALL
STREET BLOCKS AWAY
OUR KIDS ARE WITH NOTHING, NO
EDUCATION THEY'RE PHYSICALLY
THIS CLOSE, HOW DO WE MAKE THEM
WORK FOR EACH OTHER?
IT BENEFITS EVERYBODY WHEN
EVERYBODY BENEFITS
WE'RE RUNNING FINANCIAL LITERACY
NIGHTS AT SCHOOLS, WHERE
VOLUNTEERS CAN COME TO LEARN
ABOUT MONEY, AND WE ALSO HAVE A
NEW PROGRAM, INVEST IN GIRLS,
WHICH NOT ONLY HELPS GIRLS TO
GET INTRODUCED TO THE LANGUAGE
AND GRAMMAR OF FINANCE, BUT ALSO
TAKES THEM TO PLACES,
INTRODUCING THEM TO THE WORLD OF
FINANCE, TO PEOPLE LIKE YOU, ME
AND SOME OF THE WOMEN HERE AT
CNBC
SO THAT THEY CAN SEE THERE'S A
POSSIBILITY OF AN INTERESTING
CAREER WORKING IN FINANCE.
>> YOU POINT OUT THAT FAMILIES
OF PROFESSIONALS, THEY HAVE 30
MILLION MORE WORDS THAN KIDS ON
WELFARE.
A LOT OF THOSE WORDS OF
FINANCIAL RELATED.
THOSE WORDS CAN BE SCARY
SOMETIMES EVEN TO ADULTS
HOW DO WE DE-INTIMIDATE OR MAKE
IT LESS SCARY?
>> I THINK WE NEED TO TALK ABOUT
IT MORE.
ONCE YOU START SPEAKING IT,
LEARNING THE WORDS, IT'S LESS
SCARY.
YOU DON'T NEED TO KNOW THE
COMPLICATED STUFF.
YOU NEED TO KNOW, HELLO, PLEASE,
THANK YOU, AND WHERE'S THE
BATHROOM
IF WE CAN TAKE THE KIDS BASIC
LANGUAGE OF GRAMMAR AND FINANCE,
SAME AS WE -- THEN THEY'RE NOT
AFRAID, NOT TO ASK THE QUESTION,
OR MAKE UP WORDS DURING
SEGMENTS
>> THEY CAN DO THAT, TOO.
>> NAN MORRISON, A GREAT TOPIC.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING M