- You did good, buddy.
You played it right.
I wouldn't have gone on.
That's it!
Thanks to Jan Lambourne,
Emmitt Smith.
He's gonna be taking Justin
to a celebrity invitational
golf tournament.
Justin Uhart picked the case
based on a fortune cookie,
and he's walking out of here
with $120,000.
No matter what happened
tonight,
Justin came in a hero,
he was gonna leave a hero.
We'll see you next time right
here on "Deal or No Deal."
[cheers and applause]
male announcer: Tonight,
a military wife and mom
has a dream to return home...
- You wanna go back
to Michigan.
- Bring me home!
announcer:
With a million dollars!
- Yes!
- This is bigger than ever.
Each case can change
your future.
- Oh, my gosh!
No deal!
announcer: But will she
crack under the pressure
of an incredible
new game twist?
- I would like to
counter-offer.
- You just handed the game
over to her.
- She wants me gone.
announcer: It's an
unbelievable ending.
- How amazing is that?
- Oh, my God!
announcer: From Universal
Orlando Resort,
heart-pounding thrills and
hair-raising adventure await.
It's "Deal or No Deal."
[cheers and applause]
- Welcome, everybody!
I'm Howie Mandel!
I can't tell you
how excited I am
to be back hosting
a brand-new season
of "Deal or No Deal,"
or, as I like to call it,
my dream job.
[laughter]
It really is.
I get to give away $1 million.
They also let me do
real cool things...
like this.
Ladies, please!
[cheers and applause]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
Hello, ladies.
- Hello, Howie.
- Right back at ya.
Now let's meet
a brand-new player
with a brand-new chance
to win life-changing money--
Courtney Schlaud!
How are ya?
- Hello! How are you, Howie?
- Welcome to "Deal or No Deal."
- Thank you!
[screaming]
- They love you.
Tell me a little bit
about yourself.
- My name's Courtney Schlaud.
- Right.
- I'm originally from
Owosso, Michigan,
and I miss Michigan so much!
- Oh, you don't live there now?
- I do not live there now.
We're currently living
in Southern California
with my daughter Payton,
who's five.
My husband's
in the Marine Corps.
I cannot wait to move back
to Michigan after he retires,
and I actually have
a snow shovel of hope
in our garage right now still.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
A snow shovel of hope?
- Yeah.
- Because you miss snow?
- I miss it!
It's hot and dry!
- Right. [laughs] I love it.
I was born in Canada,
and I don't have to
shovel driveways.
I love that you're hoping
to get back into the snow.
That's so different.
- Yes!
Yes.
- But I love that.
I wanna know if you won
a million dollars,
what would you do?
- Oh, my gosh.
Buy a house on a lake
in Michigan,
be closer to my parents,
namely,
and my best friends
are out there.
- The Michiganers.
- The Michiganders.
- Michiganders?
Is that what they're called?
- Yes.
- Are you ready?
- I'm ready, Howie.
- Let's go, Courtney!
You a big fan of this game?
- Huge fan!
- Huge fan.
- Yes.
- All right.
Well, I'm excited you're here.
All right.
We have 26 ladies
holding 26 cases.
Each of those cases is holding
a different amount of money
packed by a third party.
We don't know what case
is holding what amount.
What we do know
is that one of the cases
is holding $1 million...
all the way down to a penny.
Now, all you have to do
is find the case
with $1 million.
- Okay! Let's do this!
- Pick a case.
- I pick case number four.
- Case number four.
That's Brenda. Brenda.
- Good luck!
- All right.
- There it is!
- First of all,
I wanna ask you
was there a reason
you chose four?
- Yes. My birthday
is on March 4th,
so it's always been
a lucky number.
- Right. And this is like
a big birthday party, isn't it?
- Ah...yes!
- Yes. This is like
a birthday party.
- Big birthday party!
- But you can't
open up your present
until the party starts.
And the way the party starts
is we start by opening
those cases.
What's ever in those cases
is not in yours.
Let's start by opening up
six cases.
- Six cases? Right.
I pick case number ten!
- Case number ten is Vaeda.
You want small amounts,
because you want the
big amount right here.
Vaeda, open your case.
- You got one penny in there,
right?
- 10,000. That's good.
- That's...good!
- All right, five more cases.
- Okay.
18.
- Elissa.
Open your case.
- I'm from Canada,
and sometimes I'm in L.A.
and I'm like, "Could use
a good blizzard," you know?
- Right.
- Beautiful!
- Well, then go buy yourself
a shovel of hope.
[laughter]
Open your case.
- Small number!
Yes!
- You made her dance.
- Yes.
- Four more.
- Could I get
case number...17?
- Ashley, open your case.
- Little!
Little.
Aaah!
Oh, my God!
- Can I get a name
for what you're doing there?
- Kinda a shimmy-shake.
Little shimmy.
- A shimmy-shake.
- Shimmy goin' on. Get excited.
- All right.
Make her shimmy--three more.
- Okay. Case number three.
- Katie, open the case.
- Little number.
Little one.
[squealing]
Whoo!
- Okay, two more cases.
- Um...case number 24.
- Kizzi, open your case.
- Come on, little!
[bass notes]
- Ooh.
[audience groans]
- Oh, no!
- That's a low blow.
- It's okay!
- That's okay.
- It's okay.
- Because most of the big
amounts are in, but...
it also includes
the $1 million.
Okay, one more case.
- 25.
- Summer, last case
in the first round.
- Come on, Summer!
Little number.
[bass notes]
Oh!
- It's okay, though.
- Okay. All right.
- I'm looking at this.
Look what you did.
Was there a reason for this?
You like parted the white sea.
[laughter]
Look what you did.
- Felt the middle a little bit.
- The middle is gone.
- It's gone!
- It's gone.
- [murmurs, sighs]
- You know how this goes,
right?
Everybody here wants your
birthday present to be
the $1 million case.
[cheers and applause]
- Thank you!
Thanks!
- When I say everybody,
I don't mean everybody.
There's one person here
who does not want that,
and that is that young lady
up there.
She is our banker.
[audience boos]
Hello.
She wants to buy that case
for as cheap as possible.
- Boo!
- Hello.
[suspenseful music]
Okay.
All right.
Um, she's got an offer.
But she says,
"Before I tell you the offer,"
um, she wants to fulfill
a dream you have.
I think this is maybe
a bargaining chip for her,
'cause she wants you
to leave right now.
So what do you have
for Courtney?
I hear footsteps.
- Ooh!
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Snow.
[laughter]
[energetic rhythm]
[Howie chuckles]
- Should I get on the floor
and lay in it?
[laughter]
- Okay.
The first offer is $16,000.
- $16,000.
- A lotta money.
- It is.
- This is "Deal or No Deal"
2.0.
- Sure.
- Our little twist is
you have an opportunity
to counter-offer.
But you can only do that
once in a game.
- All right.
- Right. You gotta make it
reasonable
if you want her to take it.
If she does take it,
you sell her the case,
and you go home.
If she says "No deal,"
the game continues.
In this case,
to continue the game,
you have to open up
another five cases.
- Okay.
- Courtney Schlaud,
deal or no deal?
- No deal!
- 16,000,
if you think about it,
is a fair chunk of change.
However,
look at the game board.
- Still great.
- So...we're thinking no deal!
- No deal.
Courtney Schlaud,
trying to make her way
back to Michigan.
That's what it's all about
for you, right?
- Well, my very best friend
and my parents are there.
Um...I was actually sick
through my 20s,
and I watched my parents
go to work every day
just to cover
the insurance premiums
for me to get treatment
to sleep on their couch
18 hours a day.
It took about six years
for me to get better.
I never thought I'd get
married, go to school,
have a baby,
and...look now!
[cheers and applause]
- Wow. That's amazing.
- I want a portion of whatever
I get to go to my parents.
- Right.
Oh, that's so wonderful.
- Yes.
- To give back.
[applause]
- So...fingers crossed!
- All right, five more
cases to open.
- Okay. How 'bout
lucky number seven?
- Small amount.
Open the case.
- [mouthing words]
- That's okay.
- That's less than
the big ones before.
- It's less than my million.
- You got four more cases.
- Number 14.
- Olga, small amount!
- The $1.00.
1.00!
- $1.00.
[bass notes]
[audience groans]
That's a tough one
- Oh, that hurt.
- There's still a great safety
net of 200,000 to $400,000.
All right, three more cases.
- All right, number 26.
- Michelle, open your case.
- $1.00. You've gotta
have the dollar in it.
Please!
Oh!
Sassy! Sassy.
- She is sassy.
Sassy Michelle.
Two more cases.
- Let's get sometimes
unlucky 13 off the board.
- That is Mahogany Lox.
- Come on, girl!
- Open your case!
- Little, sister!
- Ooh.
- Eek!
It's all right.
- All right.
The million dollars
is still in play.
Okay? One more case.
- All right.
We'll go number one.
- Soraya, open your case.
- Yes!
[cheers and applause]
- All right.
Here is the offer.
Hello?
- I'm ready for the weather!
[laughter]
- Okay.
You think the offer
went up or down?
You did knock out
a couple of big ones there.
- I do believe it went up.
- Why?
- Because I want it to be up!
[laughter, cheers]
- You are right,
and it's because
the million dollars
is still in play--that's why.
And it went up to $26,000.
The million dollars
is still in play.
I told you, you got a big
decision here, and it's real.
And you have an opportunity
to counter-offer if you want.
You don't have to
do this alone.
You brought some supporters.
- Yes!
- All right.
Hi!
- Hi.
- What's your name?
- My name is Acton.
I'm a fellow Marine wife.
- Oh, wonderful.
- We met through our husbands.
We've done every crazy thing
in life that the Marine Corps
can handle.
We've been there together,
all through it all.
- Whoo! Yeah!
- Okay.
And you are?
- My name is Kristika.
I met Courtney
in the last year.
She is a great mom.
Like with Payton, she turns
everything into a positive.
It could be bad,
but she'll turn it around.
She is awesome.
- And who are you, young man?
- How you doing?
- I'm doing great.
- I'm John.
I married the love of my life.
- Yeah!
- First of all,
thank you for your service.
- Thank you for
the support, Howie.
She supported me
through thick and thin,
eight years of marriage,
multiple deployments.
And we're all here
to support you.
We're all here for your day.
- Yeah!
- I love you.
- She's dreamed about this day
for a long time.
Happy Courtney Day!
- Whoo!
- Happy Courtney Day!
You got emotional when they
were talking about you.
- Yeah.
My husband has been in the
Marine Corps for 20 years now.
[cheers and applause]
And I couldn't be more proud.
I know I talk about Michigan,
but he and my daughter
are my home,
and we're gonna go
wherever he does.
And we just hope to land
in Michigan.
- You support going back
to Michigan, sir?
- I do support going home
to Michigan
when I do retire,
whenever that is.
And this million dollars that's
in that number four case
is gonna help us.
- Yeah!
- All right, Courtney Schlaud,
deal or no deal?
- $26,000.
- 26. There's three up there.
No deal. No deal.
[overlapping chatter]
- We've got three big
players on the board.
So Mr. Howie...
- Mrs. Courtney?
[laughter]
- No deal!
- No deal.
She's on her way
to million dollars
when we come back.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
announcer:
A game-changing moment...
- Oh, my God!
announcer: That knocks Howie
off his feet.
- Oh, my gosh.
I gotta sit down.
My legs are weak.
And this is your game!
announcer: Is this military
wife strong enough to recover?
[dramatic music]
Feel the clarity of
non-drowsy Claritin
and relief from
Symptoms caused
by over
200 indoor
and outdoor
allergens.
Like those
from buddy.
Because stuffed
animals
are clearly no substitute
for real ones.
Feel the clarity.
And Live Claritin clear.
Most people
know State Farm
for home and
auto insurance.
We've also won five
J.D. Power awards in a row
for life insurance.
You know what
you're not winning
any awards for?
Your diet.
Super weird.
( ♪♪ )
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
I'm Ken Jacobus and I switched
to the Spark Cash Card
from Capital One.
I earn unlimited 2% cash back on
everything I buy.
And last year, I earned $36,000
in cash back.
Which I used to offer health
insurance to my employees.
What's in your wallet?
♪ ♪
There are roadside attractions.
And then there's our
world-famous
ON-road attraction.
If you've never seen
yourself in a Mercedes,
you've never seen these offer.
Lease the 2019 GLC 300
for just $479 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz
Spring Event.
Hurry in before April 30th.
[dynynamic music]
- Welcome back
to "Deal or No Deal."
This is Courtney Schlaud.
You wanna go back to Michigan.
You wanna see your parents.
You wanna see your best
friends.
Your husband said
Courtney Day--
it's all about a celebration.
Based on what your husband
called it,
this is what we're gonna
do for you.
Happy Courtney Day!
- Yay!
- Little something.
- [chanting] Courtney Day!
Courtney Day!
- All right.
Four cases to open.
Three big amounts.
- Okay.
- Pick a case.
- Supporters,
anything screaming to you?
- I think you should go
with number 11.
- All right, number 11!
- Brittany, open the case.
- Low, low, low, low.
- Small amount, small amount.
- Number 22!
- Anchal!
- Little!
- Open the case.
Something small...
That's good!
- Good!
- Two more cases to open.
Three big amounts
still on the board.
- Been working for you.
- Up the middle?
- Up the middle.
- Okay.
- Number two?
- Taylor, open the case.
- $1.00.
- [chanting] Small, small,
small, small, small.
- Small, small, small!
Small amount.
Yes! One more case to open!
- Yes!
- She's dancing.
- We gotta
make you shimmy-shake.
- I'm not a--I can't--
I don't know how to--
- Get a little neck into it.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, yeah. Got it.
I got it.
Oh, yeah.
Got it, got it.
Oh, my God.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
I think they're laughing
with me, right, not at me.
- With.
- I hope so.
- Okay. One case.
- 23 has been lucky
for me in the past.
- 23. Anne Julia.
You know, you gotta avoid
the million dollars.
You know what would be
a beaut is $10.00.
Open your case.
- $10!
- $10! $10!
[suspenseful music]
- Yes!
[cheers and applause]
Yeah-ea!
- Yeah, well.
Ah. That was me
doing The Shimmy.
The biggest amount you knocked
out of that round
was $25,000.
That's a good round.
All the big money remained.
Call us.
[phone rings]
[audience boos]
Hello.
Mm-hmm.
All right.
As long as the million dollars
stays in play,
you may shimmy,
but that makes her shake.
- Yeah!
[applause]
The new offer...
is almost double.
The new offer--$57,000.
- Okay. That's a lot.
- That's a lotta money.
What can $57,000 do for ya?
- I wish you knew the state
of my husband's car.
And he drives it just so
he can put our daughter
in different activities
and all of that,
and he sacrifices so much.
- Would $57,000 get you
back to Michigan?
- It could, but I know
it could be much more.
[applause]
- Courtney Schlaud,
deal or no deal?
[overlapping shouting]
- 57,000...
- $57,000 is a lot of money,
but I think this is
Courtney's Day.
I think she wants to go
for that million.
There's a lotta other offers
up there.
[applause]
- Howie...no deal!
- No deal. Wow.
- Three cases. Pick a case.
- 19!
- Is there a reason for 19?
- A good age,
right before I got sick.
A lot of freedom at 19.
- Okay.
- We're open for the $10.
- We're looking for anything
from the left side.
Natasha, open the case.
- Left side!
[suspenseful music]
- Aah!
Oh, my God! Thanks!
- Two more. Two more.
- Um...
number five.
My daughter's five years old.
- Lani, open the case.
- $10! $10!
$10!
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Yes!
- [chanting]
Courtney, Courtney, Courtney!
- Whoo!
- [chanting] Courtney,
Courtney, Courtney, Courtney!
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, thank you.
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, you're all amazing!
[laughter]
Number eight,
you've got my $10.
- Anything but those
bottom right amounts.
And I promise you,
your next offer will be more.
The answer is in this case.
We need something
from the left side.
- Yes! $10.
- Neka, open the case.
- Left side!
- Yes!
- [chanting] Courtney Day!
Courtney Day!
- How amazing is that?
- Yes!
- Isn't that great?
Ha ha ha ha.
She's gonna--she's gonna
go for the million
when we come back!
Get me a shovel!
[energetic music]
- Ooh! You guys ready?
announcer: Before her battle
with the banker,
- That's really tall.
What did I agree to?
announcer: Courtney Schlaud
takes a thrilling ride
down the twists and turns
of Universal's Volcano Bay
Water Theme Park.
(Steel-drum ringtone sounds)
Hello?
Hello there!
Almond Joy is Tropi-Calling!
When you need a taste
of vacation,
pick up!
Every day, visionaries are
creating the future.
So, every day,
we put our latest technology
and unrivaled network to work.
The United States Postal
Service makes more
e-commerce deliveries
to homes
than anyone else
in the country.
e-commerce deliveries
to homes
IF YOU HAVE A GARDEN YOU KNOW,
WEEDS ARE LOWDOWN
LITTLE SCOUNDRELS.
WITH ROUNDUP SURE SHOT WAND
YOU DON'T NEED TO
STOOP TO THEIR LEVEL.
DRAW THE LINE.
THE SURE SHOT WAND EXTENDS
WITH A PROTECTIVE SHIELD
TO PINPOINT THOSE
PESKY BEDFELLOWS.
IT LETS YOU KILL WHAT'S
BAD RIGHT DOWN TO THE ROOT
WHILE COMFORTABLY
GUARDING THE GOOD.
DRAW THE LINE WITH THE
ROUNDUP SURE SHOT WAND.
ROUNDUP BRAND.
TRUSTED FOR OVER 40 YEARS.
(MEG VO)
I can just suck up my
endometriosis pain...
Or I can...
(DIANE VO)
I can keep apologizing...
Or I can...
(SHERRY VO)
I can hope my pain gets better
on its own...
Or I can talk to
my gynecologist today!
(AVO)
You didn't choose to have
endometriosis...
but you can choose to ask
if ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA is specifically
developed for women
with moderate to severe
endometriosis pain.
In clinical trials,
ORILISSA was proven to reduce 3
common types of
endometriosis pain,
painful periods,
pelvic pain in between
periods,
and pain with sex.
Don't use ORILISSA if you are or
may be pregnant,
have osteoporosis,
severe liver disease, or are
taking drugs like
cyclosporine or gemfibrozil.
It may cause abnormal
liver tests.
ORILISSA may change your
periods, making it hard
to know if you are pregnant.
It does not prevent pregnancy.
Use birth control that does not
contain hormones.
ORILISSA may cause suicidal
thoughts or actions.
It may also cause bone loss.
Ask your gynecologist if
ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA. Made for endo pain.
[exciting music]
- Welcome back to
"Deal or No Deal."
I'm standing right here
with a Michigander,
Courtney Schlaud.
You had an incredible round.
The last round, the most
you knocked out was $750.
- Go Courtney!
- That was amazing!
- You remember what
your last offer was?
- I don't.
[laughter]
- I'm gonna tell you.
It was $57,000.
- $57,000.
- And you turned it down.
You said no.
- Yes.
- You had a great round.
You know that.
There's the new offer.
- There it is.
[audience boos]
[phone ringing]
- Hello.
[not audible]
Okay.
- She's mad.
She's not happy.
- No!
Which should make you happy.
- Yeah!
- $92,000.
[audience shouting]
- That's a lot!
[dramatic music]
That is so much money.
- That's a lot of money
up there,
but you still have a lot
of money left on that board.
[cheers and applause]
- Courtney Schlaud.
- Yes.
- Deal...
or no deal?
- No!
- Don't counter.
- Those three big players
are still up there...
Two more case--
Two more cases?
Two more?
[audience shouting]
Two more cases?
Howie...
No deal!
- Wow.
- I'm nervous but good.
- You just turned down
a ton 'o money.
Whew!
- There's a lot more up there
waiting for me.
- Just keep the million,
and we're good.
- You gotta open up two cases.
- I'm...
going for number 20.
- Amanza, stay away from
the big amounts.
Open your case.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- That's okay.
- Okay.
- Okay. Okay.
- One more.
- Number nine!
- Patricia.
Each case can change
your future.
It would be amazing
if it was the thousand.
- Yes.
- Patricia, open your case.
[cheering]
- Come on, Patricia!
- Come on, Trish.
Come on, Trisha.
[cheers and applause]
- That's so amazing.
That's so amazing.
[cheers and applause]
- Good work.
- Oh!
- You're getting emotional.
- Yes!
Raising a child,
there's all the "what ifs"
and what you want to
give to them.
You don't think about
yourself much.
So, priorities.
Always for my baby girl.
- But more importantly,
if you won a million dollars,
it would definitely
get you back
to helping your parents,
it would get you back
to Michigan so you could
see your best friend.
- I miss my Amber so hard.
- There is so much at stake.
- Yeah.
- And we're about to find out
what all that is
when we come back.
♪ ♪
announcer:
As Courtney's battle
for the million continues...
- You've got a 50/50 chance
of at least $300,000.
- So much money.
announcer: She's reminded why
there's no place like home.
- I'm gonna tell you
to look at that person.
- Oh, my God!
- That is a total surprise.
SARAH'S LAST TUITION
PAYMENT, SENT OFF.
FEELING GOOD?
OH YEAH.
NOW I'M READY TO
FOCUS ON MY PROJECT.
♪ ♪ ♪
THIS IS WHY WE PLAN.
YOU NEVER CEASE
TO AMAZE ME, MAYA.
SEE HOW INVESTING WITH A J.P.
MORGAN ADVISOR CAN HELP YOU.
VISIT YOUR LOCAL CHASE BRANCH.
[exciting music]
- Well, welcome back!
It's Courtney Schlaud Day!
- Whoo!
- We're celebrating
Courtney Schlaud Day
right now with one of
the most amazing boards
I have ever seen.
And the reason it's one of
the most amazing boards
I've ever seen is because
you've got a 50/50 chance
of walking out of here
with at least $300,000.
You said during the break
that it feels like a dream.
- Yes.
- And you know,
at "Deal or No Deal,"
besides with the money,
it's a show where--
where we want your dreams
to come true.
And I don't know
if this helps.
You know, we gave you
a little bit of snow.
We gave you
a nice little sign.
- That's fantastic.
- How 'bout a little taste
of Michigan?
Would you like that?
- Okay...
- All right.
Here's what I'm going to do.
- 'Kay.
- I'm gonna tell you
to look at that person...
- Oh, my God!
- That's Amber!
That's her best friend!
She had no idea
that her best friend
would be there.
Absolutely no idea.
- I love you so much!
- You need to turn around.
- What?
- Oh, my God!
- Her parents!
That's her parents.
- Stop it, stop it, stop it!
[squeals] You're here!
How?
- That is her parents.
That is a total surprise.
- [chanting] Courtney Day!
- This is your family.
These are--
This is your best friend.
- This one has been
posting stuff,
making herself look busy.
[laughter]
Hi!
[phone rings]
- Ooh!
- Remember...
these offers are real.
Real.
- Sass her.
- Hello.
[suspenseful music]
[chuckles] Okay.
She says
in terms of holidays,
Courtney Day--
not her favorite.
- Aw, boo!
- You're welcome!
[laughter, applause]
- Okay.
- [whispers]
Oh, my gosh.
[suspenseful music]
- You know what
this money means.
It means a lot.
You've seen your daughter
and your friend,
your wife, and your friend--
you've seen her turn down
life-changing money.
It's tough.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yes.
- You're at a place
in the game now where you have
to open one case at a time.
- Yeah!
[cheers and applause]
- You believe you have
the million in your case?
- My number four.
My number four!
- Do you believe it enough
and feel it enough
to turn down
$173,000?
- One more case!
- One more case. If you do
knock out the million,
you'll never get an offer
that high.
Mom, what would you
tell your daughter to do?
- Mama!
[no sound]
[laughter]
- [high voice]
What do you want?
[laughter]
- She's lost her voice.
She lost her voice--because
this means a lot, right?
- Oh, yes.
- It does.
- And $173,000 is a huge
amount of money.
You have an opportunity
to counter-offer.
If you do counter,
it's gotta be reasonable
to have her accept it.
If she says no deal,
the game goes on, and you
open up one more case.
Oh, you're taking off your
sweater. You're getting hot.
[laughter]
I might keep it on,
because it's been known
to snow in here.
[laughter]
- I have watched you
put your life on hold
to serve everyone around you.
And you know what?
You deserve this.
Girl, you gotta get
one more case out of there.
- Courtney Schlaud...
deal...
or no deal?
[overlapping shouting]
- So much money.
- No deal.
- Howie.
[suspenseful music]
No deal!
Oh, my gosh!
- Yes! Yes!
- If you open up
anything from the left side,
that number
will keep going up.
[cheers and applause]
- Number 15.
- That's Madi.
- Left side.
Anything from the left.
Madi, open the case.
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- You got this! You got this!
- I can't move!
[audience chanting]
Courtney Day, Courtney Day,
Courtney Day,
Courtney Day, Courtney Day!
[phone rings]
[audience boos]
[ringing]
- Hello.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Come on, Courtney!
- Courtney.
- I will tell you this.
You have an amazing board.
You, Courtney,
have been very,
very lucky.
- Yes.
[cheers and applause]
- You have a big offer.
You don't have to
say it out loud,
but I'm gonna tell you
what the offer is.
- Oh! Ha ha ha ha ha!
[inaudible]
Ooh!
- Do you wanna sit--
[laughter]
You need to sit down?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, she needs to sit down.
- Yes! She did this.
She did this!
- You want me to tell her?
- Yes!
- Or you wanna tell her?
- No, you tell her.
[laughter]
- Okay.
$266,000!
More than
1/4 of a million dollars,
guaranteed.
- [chanting] One more case!
One more case!
- The one question mark
is what's in...
here?
- It's my million.
My million.
It is.
- Courtney Schlaud.
- Yes, sir.
- Deal...or no deal?
[overlapping shouting]
- Courtney, counter!
Counter!
- One more case.
No deal!
- This is amazing.
A million dollars
still in play
when we come back.
♪ ♪
announcer: With three
huge amounts still in play...
- One of the most amazing
boards I have ever seen.
announcer:
Courtney risks it all...
- That is so much money.
No deal!
announcer: And takes control.
- I'd like to counter-offer.
She wants me gone.
-And we welcome back Gary,
who's already won three cars,
two motorcycles, a boat,
and an R.V.
I would not want to pay
that insurance bill.
[ Ding ]
-Oh, I have Progressive,
so I just bundled everything
with my home insurance.
Saved me a ton of money.
-Love you, Gary!
-You don't have to buzz in.
It's not a question, Gary.
On March 1, 1810 --
[ Ding ]
-Frédéric Chopin.
-Collapsing in 226 --
[ Ding ]
-The Colossus of Rhodes.
-[ Sighs ] Louise Dustmann --
[ Ding ]
-Brahms' "Lullaby,"
or "Wiegenlied."
-When will it end?
[ Ding ]
-Not today, Ron.
We're Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh and
you may remember us from...
-When will it end?
[ Ding ]
Your very first sandwich,
Your move-in-day...feast.
Your bold canine caper.
[child] That's not for you,
Bandit!
Your dinner in the dark.
Your mammoth masterpiece.
[whispering] Your 3:47 AM snack.
And...whatever happened here...
Because we make Deli Fresh
with all the good of the deli,
no artificial preservatives and
no added nitrates or nitrites.
Make every sandwich count
with Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh.
Let's see, ALEVE is
proven better on pain
than Tylenol Extra Strength.
And last longer
with fewer pills.
So why am I still
thinking about this?
I'll take Aleve.
ALEVE.
Proven better on pain.
I like to make my life easy.
( ♪♪ )
Romo mode.
(Beep)
(Bang)
Good luck
with that one.
Yes!
That's why I wear
Skechers Slip-Ons.
They're effortless.
Just slip them
right on and off.
Skechers
Slip-Ons,
with
Air-Cooled
Memory Foam.
[exciting music]
- All right, welcome back
to "Deal or No Deal"
for our celebration
of Courtney Schlaud Day.
This is the game of a lifetime.
She just turned down--
You, young lady,
just turned down more than
1/4 of a million dollars,
a guarantee--
- Sounds so bad.
- But it can also end up
being great.
- Is it okay that I don't
feel my hands right now?
- Yes.
- Is that normal?
- Uh, no, but we do have
a medic.
- I'm good.
- All right. One case.
- I choose...
case six.
- That's Megan.
- Come on, sister.
- $10 or $100 would be huge.
- Yeah.
- Bottom right would drop you.
Open the case.
[crowd commotion]
[suspenseful music]
- $10.
♪ ♪
- Oh, no!
- Courtney!
[cheers and applause]
- [chanting] Courtney Day,
Courtney Day, Courtney Day!
- All right.
- Courtney Day!
- All right. It is crazy.
Because now look at
that board.
You have a
three out of four chance
of having $300,000,
or more, in this case.
A three out of four.
There are four cases left.
One of them is holding $100.
Is the $100 up there,
or is the $100 here?
This is about to get huge.
It has been huge.
This is bigger than ever.
Are you ready for this?
Are you ready?
[phone rings]
[audience murmurs]
[ringing]
Hello.
- Courtney!
- Gonna brace myself.
- Okay. Okay.
Okay.
All right.
She needs you to leave.
- Whoa!
- [exhales]
- Boy.
[suspenseful music]
- Wait for the deal.
- $342,000.
- Whoo!
- You made a $342,000 face.
- That is so much money.
- It is so much money.
- But look at that
stinking board.
- Oh, girl, girl!
- That is an amazing board,
probably one of the best
boards I've ever seen.
That being said,
$100 is still on that board.
- Correct.
- Which means...
this could be the $100.
- Oh...
- It can be.
Mom, how are you holding up?
- I'm okay.
- How you doing, Mom?
[laughing]
- How can you counter-offer?
- Here, come here.
Okay.
[cheers and applause]
That's the banker,
and what she has to do
is she has to
make her an offer,
but it's got to be
a reasonable offer.
If she takes it,
she writes you that check,
and you go home
and you give her the case.
Oh!
If she says no deal,
all the money's off the table,
and she has to open
one more case.
- Okay.
- You're welcome.
Thank you, I'll be all--
all night.
[cheers and applause]
Courtney Schlaud...
you must answer
this question now.
Deal...or no deal?
[overlapping shouting]
[suspenseful music]
- You should counter!
♪ ♪
- Counter at $400,000.
- Howie...
♪ ♪
- No deal!
- Oh, my--oh, my gosh.
One case.
- Okay.
- [chanting]
Courtney Day, Courtney Day!
Courtney Day,
- One case.
Oh, my gosh.
One case.
Oh, my gosh, I don't know--
I gotta sit down.
Go ahead.
Pick a case.
- Me too.
- Pick a case.
- Can I join you?
- You can sit with me.
- Courtney, take a load off!
[cheers and applause]
- [indistinct]
- Come on, Courtney,
you got this.
[laughter]
- All right, pick a case.
♪ ♪
[woman laughs]
- 12!
[cheers and applause]
- All right,
if that 100's in there,
you are about to go to
the stratosphere
and on your way to $1 million.
It all depends on this case.
And this case will be opened...
when we come back.
- No!
- Yes!
Yes.
Reese's eggs are back
and we hid them
somewhere you'll never find...
Sike! We put them everywhere.
Grocery stores and
supermarkets, gas stations,
and chiropractor's offices,
bowling alleys,
and grocery stores,
which we already mentioned...
Not Sorry, Reese's.
I'm Ken Jacobus and I switched
to the Spark Cash Card
from Capital One.
I earn unlimited 2% cash back on
everything I buy.
And last year, I earned $36,000
in cash back.
Which I used to offer health
insurance to my employees.
What's in your wallet?
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
TO BE NOBODY BUT YOURSELF IN A
WORLD WHICH IS DOING IT'S BEST
TO MAKE YOU EVERYBODY ELSE...
♪ ♪ ♪
MEANS TO FIGHT
THE HARDEST BATTLE,
WHICH ANY HUMAN BEING
CAN FIGHT AND NEVER STOP.
DOES THIS SOUND DISMAL?
IT ISN'T.
♪ ♪ ♪
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL LIFE ON EARTH.
♪ ♪ ♪
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL LIFE ON EARTH.
Oh, sir. That was my grandma's.
Don't worry, ma'am. All of your
stuff is in OK hands.
Just OK?
They don't give two and a half
stars to just anybody.
Here you go.
What's this?
It's your piano.
Hold this for a sec!
We don't have a piano.
No.
But the neighbors do.
Just OK is not OK.
Especially when it comes to you
network.
AT&T is America's best wireless
network
according to America's biggest
test.
Now with 5G Evolution.
The First Step to 5G.
More for your thing.
That's our thing.
[dynamic music]
- Welcome back to
"Deal or No Deal."
It is Courtney Schlaud Day.
This is Courtney Schlaud.
We are celebrating her.
We are celebrating her life.
You know what's making me
nervous.
- Tell me.
- This is why we're sitting.
My legs are weak.
And this is your game.
[groans]
Oh, my God, a marine.
A marine looks nervous.
Look.
You don't see marines
that look nervous.
You know what, I don't even
wanna take control of this.
You picked number 12.
- Yes, sir.
- Her name is Sarati.
One case to open.
There is a million dollars
on the board,
but there are still
$100 on the board.
You turned down $342,000.
You know what?
I don't want this
on me at all, so Courtney...
you tell Sarati when you
want her to open the case.
I'll be over there.
- Nice job, Howie.
- My heart is beating so fast.
- Sarati...
open the case!
♪ ♪
[bass notes]
That's okay!
- That's okay.
It's 300,000.
- Okay.
Still four.
- That's still good.
- Great. That's great!
- Now you have
a two out of three chance
that that case is holding
at least $400,000.
But you still have
the $100 in play.
[phone rings]
[audience murmurs]
Hello.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Ooh, she's mad,
- Okay.
Okay.
Everything...
everything in life
has a tipping point.
- Ooh!
- Is this the tipping point?
The offer now...
Is...
$425,000.
- Courtney!
[crowd commotion, shouting]
- Guarantee!
- Counter?
- I would counter with
$450,000.
- You would add $25,000.
- I would counter.
That's what I would
counter with.
- What you're saying--
for another $25,000,
it is worth the risk
of her possibly turning it down
and forcing you
to open another one.
For another $25,000.
- What if we countered with 5?
Is that a no?
- Counter with 5.
- Counter with 5?
[audience shouting]
- It's one time!
- $425,000
is a guaranteed amount.
Courtney Schlaud,
deal or no deal?
[overlapping shouting]
- I would like to
counter-offer.
- Okay.
- For $500,000.
[cheers and applause]
- Can I ask you something?
Before she calls back.
And that's in.
That's in.
You can't change that.
That is in.
Why did you do that?
- She wants me gone.
- Right.
But this can also have
$100 in it.
- Correct. My heart is telling
me counter at 500.
- All right.
- - That's all you need!
You just handed the game
over to her.
It's in her control.
Let's see what she says.
[phone rings]
[audience oohs]
[ringing]
Hello.
All right.
Okay.
- Courtney, shake it out.
[suspenseful music]
- Okay.
She said, "Courtney
"asked me to take
$1/2 million
for what's in that case."
And she said,
"So I look at the board,
"and I say to myself,
"while there's a two
out of three chance
"that the case is worth
only 400 or 100,
there's a better chance
it's not worth the million."
She said,
"Why would I do that?"
Why?
♪ ♪
- She wants my million
in this case.
- But there's a
two out of three chance
that that isn't the million.
- The beauty of the game.
[dramatic, suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- She said, "Deal."
[dinging]
[dynamic music]
♪ ♪
- [chanting] Courtney Day,
Courtney Day,
Courtney Day, Courtney Day,
Courtney Day.
- [indistinct]
- You just sold this case
for $1/2 million.
- I did.
- That's a lotta money.
But we don't know
if you made a good deal.
- Okay.
- Had you said no deal,
what would your next choice
have been?
- Sweet 16.
- Okay. Open the case.
[dramatic chords]
- Oh, my God!
- You did the perfect thing.
This is 400,000...
$100.
Your timing
was absolutely perfect!
How amazing is that?
Courtney Schlaud
shimmy and shaked her way
all the way