MIKE IN NEW YORK CITY, HOME
BUILDERS
>> THERE'S A LOT PESSIMISM
AROUND HOUSING RIGHT NOW, WE
THINK AFFORDABILITY IS GOING TO
IMPROVE AS PRICES MODERATE AND
WAGES INCREASE
>> LET'S DO FINAL TRADE, MR.
O'LEARY.
>> IT'S A SELL UNTIL WE GOT IT
OUT OF CONGRESS.
>> MINIMUM VOLATILITY, THIS IS
NOT A TRADE, IT'S MORE OF A CORE
EXPOSURE
>> I'M GOING WITH BIOTECH INDEX,
STAYING THERE.
>> STARBUCKS KEEPS CHUCKING
HIGHER TODAY
>> XLE
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
GOOD STUFF
DOW IS NOW UP 115 POINTS THAT
DOES IT FOR US
THE EXCHANGE WITH KELLY EVANS
BEGINS NOW
>>> A RALLY FOR STOCKS SUBMIT A
CALMER DAY FOR BONDS
INDEXES ARE ON PACE FOR THEIR
BEST START TO THE YEAR SINCE
THIS MORNING'S DATA SHOWING
WEAKNESS IN THE HOUSING MARKET
THAT WAS BEFORE THE BIG DROP IN
INTEREST RATES
PLUS, PRICES ARE RISING AS MUCH.
RED-HOT IPO'S.
A WAVE OF START-UPS ARE SET TO
HIT THE MARKET THAT ARE DEBAYING
WITH GIANT LOSING.
IS IT 1999 ALL OVER AGAIN?
>> THE POSITIVITY RIGHT NOW IS
THERE ALL THE SECTORS ARE HIGHER
ON THE DAY
AT ONE POINT WE WERE UP ABOUT
279 POINTS
CAN YOU SEE HERE, UP ABOUT 113
NOW.
THE POSITIVITY IS THERE, BUT NOT
NEARLY AS MUCH SO AS IT WAS
EARLIER THIS MORNING
THE S&P HANGING AROUND THE 2815
LEVEL, WE'VE BEEN WATCHING FOR
MONTHS AT THIS POINT
WATCH THAT AND THE NASDAQ UP BY
2/3 OF 1%.
ENERGY THE BEST PERFORMER ON THE
DAY TODAY, AND YOU CAN SEE HERE
OVER THE COURSE OF THE PAST
YEAR, THE ENERGY ETF, THE OIL
AND GAS EXPLORATION OF
PRODUCTION HAVE SOME ROUGH GOES.
AS OF LATE, WE'RE WATCHING THOSE
ENERGY TRADES PLAY IN HERE AS
WELL
THE WORST PERFORMER ON THE S&P
500 CARNIVAL CRUISE LINES,
EARNINGS AND SALES CAME IN
BETTER
THE OUTLOOK DISAPPOINTED
THEY CITED A HEAD WIND BECAUSE
OF FUEL PRICES
CARNIVAL SHARES OFF BY ABOUT 9%.
YOU CAN SEE THEY'RE A DOWN TREND
EVER SINCE
OUR STOCK OF THE DAY OVER TO
YOU.
>> WE'LL SEE YOU IN A BIT.
WELCOME TO THE EXCHANGE,
EVERYONE
MEANWHILE, TECH COMPANIES HAVE
ISSUED THE MOST NEGATIVE
WARNINGS ABOUT FIRST QUARTER
RESULTS OF ANY SECTOR AND THE
HIGHEST NUMBER OF WARNINGS FOR
THE STOCKS HAVE HAD A STRONG
START FOR THE YEAR
LET'S DRILL DOWN ON THIS NOW
WITH BOB POSANI.
>> NO BIG HEADLINES, WE ARE OFF
OF OUR HIGHS, EUROPE CLOSED A
HALF HOUR AGO.
BOEING IN UNDER PRESSURE TODAY
WE STARTED AT 374 FOR BOEING
WE'RE DOWN A LITTLE.
ENERGY AS A BRIGHT SPOT.
WE'RE TEN CENTS AWAY FROM $6 0E
OIL.
ENERGY STOCKS UP 2 OR 3%
WE'RE WAITING FOR BREAKOUTS.
WE'RE NOT GETTING ANY HIGH
BREAKOUTS.
STILL LITTERED WITH THE SAME
NAMES.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT CONSUMER NAMES
LIKE GENERAL MILLS AND HER
MUCHY.
WAITING FOR SOME TECH BREAKOUTS,
STILL A COUPLE POINTS AWAY
THE GLOBAL GROWTH SLOWDOWN
WE SAW INTEREST RATES GO DOWN,
THE MARKET TENDS TO DROP
TRADES MOVE UP, THE MARKET TENDS
TO STABILIZE
>> THE S&P 500 IS NOW ON TRACK
FOR ITS BEST GAIN IN 10 YEARS,
LET'S BRING IN ART HOGAN
WELCOME TO YOU BOTH.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE ABOUT THE
STRONG START TO THE YEAR THERE'S
BEEN A LOT OF NEGATIVE WARNINGS
FROM THE TECH SECTOR
IT HELPS JUST FINE
>> IT HELPS TO HAVE A BAD END TO
THE YEAR
WE HAD A TERRIBLE END.
THAT HELPS A BIT, IT ALSO HELPS
TO HAVE A YEAR WHERE YOU'RE DOWN
AND EARNINGS ARE UP 25%.
WE'VE HAD A FEW THINGS THAT HAVE
PIVOTED THIS YEAR, THAT ARE
REALLY KICK STARTED -- WE HAVE
THE FED PIVOT IN JANUARY AND GET
EVEN MORE DONE
WE'VE HAD A STABILIZATION OF THE
DOWN DRAFT OF EARNINGS
THE S&P 500 IS WHERE IT'S BEEN
AFTER THREE WEEKS.
THAT'S THE FIRST TIME WE'VE SEEN
THAT STABILIZATION
THERE'S AN IMPRESSION WE'RE
GOING TO GET A DEAL DONE WITH
CHINA.
I THINK THOSE THREE THINGS ARE
HELPING PROPEL THE MARKETS HERE.
>> THERE'S A LITTLE LESS TALK
ABOUT THE YIELD CURVE INVERSION.
IT'S REALLY THE TWO-YEAR TEN
YEAR THAT MATTERS.
>> MIKE HAS BEEN TALKING ABOUT
THIS FOR A WHILE
THIS IDEA THAT WE FOCUS ON
CERTAIN PARTS OF THE YIELD
CURVE, THOSE TELL STORIES AT
CERTAIN TIMES.
ONE OF THE THINGS WE'VE BEEN
PAYING CLOSE ATTENTION TO IS THE
IDEA THAT FINAL STOCKS
BANKS IN PARTICULAR, THE
REGIONALS, THE ONES THAT DO MORE
TRADITIONAL LENDING HAVE BEEN A
WEAK SPOT.
THAT'S BEEN TROUBLESOME.
SOME PEOPLE ARE MAKING
COMPARISONS ON A CONSISTENT
BASIS.
LIKE IN JAPAN, HAVE DEPRESSED
THE FINANCIAL SECTOR, AS WE TALK
ABOUT WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN FOR
THE COMING MONTHS, ONE PLACE THE
FOLKS ARE LOOKING BEYOND THE
YIELD CURVE ARE WHETHER OR NOT
THOSE BANKS CAN STILL THRIVE IN
AN ENVIRONMENT LIKE THAT
WHERE CYCLICALITY --
>> THE AUCTION HAPPENED AT THE
TOP OF THE HOUR RICK, HOW DID IT
GO
>> I GIVE IT AN A MINUS.
I WAS IMPRESSED WITH THIS
KICKOFF OF 113 BILLION UNTIL
SUPPLY
THE OFFER SIDE OF THE MARKET WAS
227 AND THE WENT ISSUED.
LOWER YIELD HIGHER PRICE SOLID
2.60 COVER
THAT'S AGAINST A 2.65 TEN
AUCTION AVERAGE.
AND IF YOU CONSIDER IT'S THE
BEST SINCE NOVEMBER OF 18, IT'S
NOT TOO BAD.
BY THE WAY, YOU WERE LOOKING AT
TRENDS IN BID TO COVER
THE TREND AUCTION IS 265
THE 5 AUCTION TREND IS 252
THE INDIRECT IS REALLY STELLAR,
56%, THE BEST SINCE JANUARY OF
'18.
JUST A SMITH BELOW AVERAGE,
DEALERS TAKE A SMALL 30 POINT 7%
OF THE AUCTION
TOMORROW WE'LL BE 41 BILLION 5
BUT A NICE START TO SUPPLY
>> YOU'RE NOW GIVING AN A MINUS
TO A BOND AUCTION GOING OFF
AFTER WE'VE HAD THIS BIG SLIDE
IN RATES OVER THE LAST WEEK OR
SO, GOING BACK TO THE FEDS
MEETING.
YOU'D THINK, OKAY, YIELDS ARE
FALLING AND THAT'S GETTING A
LITTLE LESS ATTRACTIVE, YOU'RE
SAYING IT'S GETTING MORE SO?
>> IT'S HARD TO GET INTO THE
PSYCHOLOGY OF INVESTORS.
IT WOULD MAKE SENSE TO ME, I
WOULD BE MORE AGGRESSIVE IN
SELLING OFF RISING RATES THAN
RALLYING WITH LOWER RATES.
THEN AGAIN, IF THE MARKETS GET
IN SYNC WITH THE FED, AND THE
FED'S IN THE CANOE JUST FLOATING
FOR A WHILE, IT MAKES MORE SENSE
TO THINK ABOUT IT ALONG THOSE
LINES.
>> THE RELATIVER FORM ANSWER OF
THE TWO-YEAR YIELD VERSUS THE
IF YOU HAVE THE TWO YEAR
TRADING PRETTY CLOSE IN YIELD
FROM THE TEN YEAR WHICH WOULD
YOU RATHER BE.
>> IT'S A STRANGE PERIOD
YOU ORDINARILY DON'T THINK
YOU HAVE MORE OF A GROWTH
COVERAGE FOR THAT, INFLATION
COVERAGE RISK PREMIUM, YOU'RE
NOT SEEING ANY OF THAT RIGHT
NOW.
>> THE WORRISOME PART.
WHAT DOES IT SAY ABOUT THE
LONGER TERM PROSPECTS FOR THE
OUTLOOK FOR WHAT WE COULD SEE
FOR GROWTH AND INFLATION IN THE
5, 7 OR 10 YEARS
>> TELL US WHERE YOU THINK
INVESTORS SHOULD BE POSITIONED
WITH ALL THIS.
>> A QUICK ANSWER TO WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
WE HAVE SEEN FOR THE LAST TWO
YEARS, THE FRONT END OF THE
CURVE HAS BEEN ANCHORED TO OUR
MONETARY POLICY.
THE 10-YEAR COMPETES AGAINST THE
GLOBAL TEN-YEAR AND THE FRONT
END IS JUST COMPETING WITH EVERY
ITERATION OF WHAT THE FED SAYS
WE'VE HAD A FLAG FOR THE BETTER
PART OF 18 MONTHS NOW.
I THINK WHAT YOU HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT --
>> THE PRESIDENT ACTUALLY
SPEAKING LIVE, IMPROMPTU AT THE
CAPITOL, HE'S ON HIS WAY THERE
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE
YOU WANT TO LISTEN IN.
>> THAT WAS IT, TO LISTENING IN.
ARTHUR, FINISH YOUR THOUGHT,
PLEASE
>> ONE OF THE THINGS I ALWAYS
TELL INVEST IRS TO BE CAREFUL
OF, IT'S ATTRACTIVE TO LOOK AT
THINGS LIKE UTILITIES AND
STAPLES AND REEDS IN THIS
ENVIRONMENT.
YOU'RE SEARCHING
RIGHT NOW STAPLES IS TRADING AT
SOME OF THE LOWEST YIELDS FOR A
LONG TIME.
>> WOULD YOU AVOID THEM?
>> I THINK THEY MOVE AROUND
PRETTY QUICKLY
>> WHERE WOULD YOU BE?
>> REEDS ARE OKAY.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR YIELD,
THAT'S WHERE WE WOULD GO
AWAY FROM THAT, YOU'D LOOK AT
TECHNOLOGY, I THINK ENERGY HAS
AN UP SIDE TO IT, I THINK THAT
TECHNOLOGY IS GOING TO HAVE A
GOOD RUN HERE.
I THINK AS A COUNTER INTUITIVE
PLAN, FINANCIALS ARE VERY CHEAP.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH
>>> A MIXED BAG OF DATA IN
HOUSING TODAY, STARTS LAST
MONTH, COMING IN WEAKER THAN
EXPECTED
BUILDING PERMITS DROPPING AS
WELL
NONE OF THIS AFFECTS THE RECENT
DROP IN RATES FOR THE 30 YEAR
FIXED MORTGAGE IN THE LAST FEW
WEEKS.
>> THE CHIEF ECONOMIST AT THE
NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF
REALTORS
DIANA, FIRST TO YOU, IN A WAY,
IT'S NOT A DROP, THE SLOWER
INCREASE IN HOME PRICES, PLUS
LOW RATES COULD HELP
AFFORDABILITY AND THE MARKET,
RIGHT?
>> IT COULD HELP THE MARKET, IF
YOU'RE GOING INTO THE SPRING
MARKET RIGHT NOW, AND HAVE YOU
THE LOWEST RATES WE'VE SEEN IN
OVER A YEAR, AND YOU SEE THE
PRICE GAINS SHRINKING, IT'S A
GREAT TIME TO GET IN TO BE A
BUYER.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO BUY?
>> WE SAW HOUSING STARTS DROP
YEAR OVER YEAR
THE BUILDERS NEED TO STEP UP
OBVIOUSLY, CREATE MORE ENTRY
LEVEL HOUSING, WHAT IS AVAILABLE
FOR SALE IS ON THE PRICIER END
EVEN THAT DROP IN MORTGAGE RATES
IS NOT ENOUGH TO MAKE UP FOR
THAT PRICING MARKET.
>> I'M CURIOUS IF YOU CAN SPEAK
TO THE REGIONAL DYNAMICS, AND IF
THE SALT CAP IS HAVING A
NEGATIVE EFFECT ACROSS
CALIFORNIA AND NEW YORK IN
PARTICULAR
IS THAT PART OF WHY THOSE
MARKETS ARE SOFTENING WITH OTHER
PARTS DOING WELL
WHAT ARE YOU SEEING PLAYING OUT
ACROSS THE COUNTRY
>> THE MARKET IS A SLOWER
MARKET, AND NO DOUBT THE
LIMITATION ON SALT IS HAVING AN
IMPACT ON THE HIGHER END MARKET.
AND CONSEQUENTLY, THE
NORTHEASTERN STATES OF NEW YORK,
CONNECTICUT AND NEW JERSEY
SOFTER
CALIFORNIA, I WOULD SAY IS MORE
AFFORDABILITY ISSUES
RIGHT NOW WE ARE SEEING A
REVIVAL OF INTEREST.
ONE LOOKS AT THE CLOSING DADATA
FURTHERMORE, WE TRACK SOME OF
THE SOFTER DATA, SUCH AS OPENING
UP THE LOCK BOXES, WE HAVE A
CENTURY LOCK COMPANY THAT
MEASURES HOW MANY TIMES THE LOCK
BOXES ARE BEING OPENED TO SHOW
CLIENTS A HOME
THAT IS RISING
BUYERS ARE CLEARLY TAKING
ADVANTAGE OF THE LOWER INTEREST
RATES.
>> THAT MAY BE MY NEW FAVORITE
ECONOMIC INDICATOR
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU COULD TRACK
THE LOCK BOX ACTIVITY OUT THERE
IN THE HOUSING MARKET.
>> DIANA, SAME QUESTION TO YOU
ARE WE SEEING REGIONAL
VARIABILITY HERE OR IS IT THE
SAME MESSAGE NO MATTER WHERE YOU
LOOK
>> ALL HOUSING IS LOCAL.
IN PRICIER MARKETS IT'S GOING TO
BE MORE DIFFICULT.
IT'S JUST A QUESTION OF SUPPLY
AT THIS POINT.
WE'RE SEEING BIG MARKETS WITH
GREAT ECONOMIES.
IN DALLAS, AUSTIN, TEXAS
IN CHARLOTTE, NORTH CAROLINA OR
IN VIRGINIA WHERE YOU TALK ABOUT
THE AMAZON EFFECT.
YOU'RE SEEING GREAT DEMAND
THERE'S A LOT OF BUYER TRAFFIC
COMING THROUGH THESE HOMES
WILL THAT TRAFFIC TRANSLATE INTO
CLOSED SALES
IF MORTGAGE RATES STAY LOW, YOU
WILL SEE A MORE ROBUST SPRING.
IT WAS INTERESTING TODAY THAT
EVERYONE WAS KIND OF ON THE
FENCE, I TALKED TO A LOT OF
ANALYSTS WHO COME OUT SAYING, WE
THINK THERE'S A LOT OF DEMAND
HERE, THERE SHOULD BE ALL THIS
PENT UP DEMAND BUT WE'RE STILL
WORRIED ABOUT THAT
AFFORDABILITY.
ON THE KBRIBRIGHT SIDE, I TALKEO
ONE ANALYST WHO SAID, BIG
BUILDERS ARE STARTING TO ENTER
THE MARK PETP ESPECIALLY FOR THE
BIG PRODUCTION BUILDERS WHO CAN
BUILD A LOT OF SMALLER HOMES
MORE CHEAPLY IN A PRODUCTION
LINE
THEY'RE GOING TO BE MOVING AND
THAT IS SOME GOOD NEWS
YOU.
>> MENTIONED THE HIGH END OF THE
MARKET IS WEAK
DO YOU SEE THE LOWER END HOLDING
UP
>> LOWER END IS VERY HOT
ANYTHING THAT SHOWS UP IS BEING
GRABBED BY THE BUYERS.
SOMETIMES MULTIPLE BIDDING STILL
HANGING AROUND IN MARKETS.
THERE IS A DEMAND, ALONG THE
MILLENNIAL GENERATION IT'S JUST
A MATTER OF INVENTORY CHOICES.
THE CONSUMERS ARE SAYING THEY
WANT TO SEE FEW HOMES.
WE NEED INCREASED SUPPLY ON THE
LOWER END.
>> I THINK WE OPENED 30 LOCK
BOXES BEFORE WE FOUND ONE WE
LIKED.
>>> HERE'S WHAT ELSE IS COMING
UP
>> YOUR MUSIC, YOUR BROWSING,
YOUR HEALTH, AND NOW YOUR
FINANCES
APPLE LAUNCHES ITS OWN CREDIT
CARD, BOASTING A SLEW OF PERKS
ONE EXPERT SAYS IT'S MORE BITE
THAN BARK.
WE'RE GOING TO PARTY LIKE IT'S
MANY OF HOT IPO'S SET TO HIT THE
MARKET MAKE NO MONEY
IS THIS A REPEAT OF THE DOT COM
BUBBLE
>>> AND THE DRIVE THROUGH MAY
SOON KNOW WHAT YOU WANT TO ORDER
BEFORE YOU DO.
You're turning onto the
street
when you barely
clip a passing car.
Minor accident
—no big deal, right?
Wrong. Your insurance
company is gonna raise
your rate after the other
car got a scratch so small
you coulda fixed
it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that
pen and use it to sign up
with a different
insurance company.
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because of
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>>> WELCOME BACK, APPLE
ANNOUNCING IT'S PARTNERING WITH
GOLDMAN SACHS AND MASTERCARD
IT WILL HAVE NO FEES, CASH BACK
REWARDS PAID OUT DAILY
DYNAMIC FINANCIAL TOOLS, PLUS A
CARD MADE OUT OF TITANIUM.
IT COULD BE MORE GIMMICK THAN
GAME CHANGER
JOINING ME WITH THEIR TAKES ARE
KATE ROONEY.
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU BOTH
HERE
WHAT DOES DIFFERENTIATE APPLE
CARD FROM WHAT'S ALREADY ON THE
MARKET IF ANYTHING
>> THE BIGGEST DIFFERENTIATOR IS
THE TITANIUM CARD.
IT'S A REALLY COOL LASER EDGE.
>> COULDN'T SOMEONE ELSE COME
OUT WITH A TITANIUM CARD
TOMORROW IF THAT'S THE CASE?
>> THEY COULD.
>> WHEN YOU LOOK INTO THE MEAT
OF THIS, THE REWARDS, THE FEES,
THE INTEREST RATES
ALL THAT STUFF EXISTS ON OTHER
CARDS.
THE BIG DIFFERENTIATOR HERE IS
THE METAL ITSELF OR THE APPLE
NAME
>>.
>> THEY'RE CLEARLY LOOKING TO
SELL THE INTERFACE, THAT'S WHY I
WONDER IF IT'S A GLIMPSE OF
HAVING LARGER ASPIRATIONS P.M.
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE THAT, AND
ESPECIALLY, YOU THINK OF ALL
THESE TECH COMPANIES, THAT'S
THEIR THING, HAVING THE COOL
INTERFACE, NO FEES
THESE COOL LOOKING CREDIT CARDS.
I THINK THAT'S GOING TO BE A
CREDIT TO THIN TECH, WHY NOT GO
ON YOUR iPHONE VERSUS GOING AND
GETTING A BRAND NEW ACCOUNT, A
BRAND NEW CREDIT CARD.
>> I WONDER TOO.
YES, I UNDERSTAND IT'S JUST A
CREDIT CARD, AND IT'S NOT AS IF
APPLE IS GOING TO BECOME A BANK
TOMORROW, IS THERE A WAY IN
WHICH THEY COULD SAY -- THOSE
TYPES OF FEATURES WHERE IT'S
ROUNDING UP TO THE NEAREST
DOLLAR TO HELP YOU SAVE.
OR OTHER THINGS THAT ARE ALREADY
EMBEDDED IN THIS CARD, THAT
SUGGEST THEY CAN TAKE ON SOME OF
THOSE ASPECTS IF THEY WANTED TO.
>> I THINK SO, THE BIG WORRY IS
IF THEY EVER GOT INTO CUSTOMER
DEPOSITS
EVEN JUST THE CUSTOMER BASE IN
GENERAL, APPLE HAS A REALLY
LARGE AND LOYAL CUSTOMER BASE.
THE SECURITY ASPECTS OF THIS,
THEY DON'T HAVE A SIGNATURE,
THERE'S NO NUMBER ON THIS CARD
AS FAR AS KEEPING YOUR
INFORMATION SAFE
THEY PROVED YOU'RE ABLE TO
PROVIDE SOMETHING THAT WON'T BE
HARKED
AND IF YOU DO GET HACKED YOU'RE
GOING TO THE GENIUS BAR.
>> THERE'S NOT A NUMBER OR
CONSTANT CHANGING SECURITY CODE.
IS THIS LIKELY SOMETHING THAT
WE'RE GOING TO SEE OTHERS ADOPT?
>> IT'S BLENDING THE APP WITH A
PHYSICAL CARD.
WHAT I WOULD HAVE DONE IS GO ALL
IN ON ONE OF THESE CATEGORIES,
HAVING SOMETHING TRULY
DIFFERENTIATED IN FINTECH.
TAKE ON MINT FOR INSTANCE.
OR HAVE A MEGA SIGNUP BONUS OR
REALLY AMAZING ONGOING REWARDS
OR SOME INCREDIBLE ZERO% OFFER
THEY DID A SERIES OF HALF
MEASURES, THEY HAVE ENOUGH CASH
ON THEIR BALANCE SHEET
I WOULD HAVE GONE ALL IN ON ONE
OF THOSE
AND GAIN THAT MARKET SHARE
>> HOW WOULD YOU DO THAT RIGHT
NOW?
2% CASH BACK, 3% ON APPLE
PRODUCTS, WHAT WOULD BE A
ENOUGH
>> YOU CAN GET 2% CASH BACK ON
THE CITI DOUBLE CASH
3% ON THE MOBIL BANK CARD.
I THINK 3% CASH BACK ON
EVERYTHING WOULD HAVE GOTTEN A
LOT OF ATTENTION
MAYBE WORTH $11,000 OR MORE.
THAT WOULD GET MORE PEOPLE'S
ATTENTION.
>> BUT IT WOULD ALSO COST MONEY.
EVEN WITH THE CHASE CARD,
SAPPHIRE AND OTHERS HAVE ALMOST
DONE TOO WELL.
WE DON'T CARE, WE WANT THESE
PEOPLE FOR THE LONG RUN, IT'S
WORTH IT
CAN APPLE AFFORD FOR THIS TO BE
A LOSS LEADER?
>> IT'S A FAIR POINT
WHAT I WOULD DO FOR THE FUTURE,
I WOULD GET IN NOW, TRY TO
GOBBLE UP A TON OF MARKET SHARE,
MAYBE TAKE CASH OFF THAT BALANCE
SHEET AND GET MORE PEOPLE IN THE
DOOR, THAT'S WHAT WE'VE SEEN IN
CHINA.
THOSE SERVICES ARE REALLY
BECOMING THE RAILS THAT PROCEED
SES ALL OF THESE FINANCIAL
TRANSACTIONS.
>> THROUGH MESSAGING
>> IT'S HARD TO DO IN THE U.S.
BECAUSE OF REGULATION AND IT'S
HARD TO GET A BANK CHARTER, I
THINK THERE ARE WAYS THAT THESE
SOCIAL MEDIA COMPANIES COULD BE
DOING MORE, BECAUSE RIGHT NOW,
LIKE APPLE PAY, IT JUST
PROCESSES THROUGH THE EXISTING
RAILS.
I THINK THERE'S MORE THAT COULD
BE DONE.
>> IRWONDER ABOUT ON BOARDING
PEOPLE TOO
A CREDIT CARD IMPLIES YOU HAVE
CREDIT
WHO'S RESPONSIBLE FOR SAYING,
YOU DON'T QUALIFY FOR THE APPLE
CARD
AND IS THAT A BRAND ISSUE?
>> WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU HAVE AN
iPHONE AND CAN'T GET ACCESS TO
THE CREDIT CARD.
WHETHER THEY HAVE LARGER
INTENTIONS HERE, WE'LL SEE
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, KATE ROONEY
AND TED ROSSMAN.
>>> A LOT OF THE TECH COMPANIES
GOING PUBLIC THIS YEAR HAVE ONE
THING IN COMMON, THEY'RE NOT
MAKING MONEY
>>> SPEAKING OF 1999, McDONALD'S
IS MAKING ITS LARGEST
ACQUISITION SINCE THEN, WHEN IT
BOUGHT BOSTON MAETRK
THIS ONE IS ALL ABOUT MACHINE
LEARNING
you can, with
ShipSticks.c
om!
No more lugging your clubs
through the airport or risk
having your clubs lost or
damaged by the airlines.
Sending your
own clubs ahead
with
ShipSticks.com
makes it
fast & easy
to get to your golf destination.
With just a few clicks
or a phone call,
we'll pick up and deliver
your clubs on-time,
guaranteed,
for as low as $39.99.
ShipSticks.com saves you
time and money.
Make it simple.
Make it Ship Sticks.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO THE
EXCHANGE
BED, BATH AND BEYOND IS A BIG
STORY TODAY.
THREE DIFFERENT ACTIVIST
INVESTORS PREPARE TO REPLACE THE
COMPANY'S ENTIRE BOARD
AT THE SAME TIME, RAYMOND JAMES
IS SAYING THE COMPANY COULD BE
RIGHT FOR A MERGER OR TO BE
TAKEN PRIVATE IN THE FORESEEABLE
FUTURE
A 25% SURGE OF BBBY.
>>> ELON MUSK HAS WON A
SECURITIES LAWSUIT
TESLA UP 2 1/2% TODAY.
MEDICAID STOCKS ARE UNDER
PRESSURE FOLLOWING THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S DECISION TO
SIDE WITH TEXAS AND GOP STATE
THAT IS WANT THE WHOLE
AFFORDABLE CARE ACT THROWN OUT
MOLINA IS DOWN ALMOST 9%
>> HERE'S WHAT'S HAPPENING AT
THIS HOUR.
ACTING DEFENSE SECRETARY PATRICK
SHANAHAN APPEARING BEFORE THE
HOUSE ARMED SERVICES COMMITTEE
AFTER SIGNING OFF ON A PLAN TO
SHIFT A BILLION DOLLARS TO
BOARDER FENCE CONSTRUCTION
THE COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN OPPOSED
THE MOVE
>> WHAT EVERYONE FEELS ABOUT THE
BOARDER WALL, TO LOOK AT THE
PENTAGON AS SORT OF A
PIGGYBANK/SLUSH FUND WHERE YOU
CAN GO IN AND GRAB MONEY WHEN
YOU NEED IT, REALLY UNDERMINES
THE CREDIBILITY OF THE ENTIRE
DOD BUDGET.
>>> DUKE UNIVERSITY HAS CHOSEN
TO SETTLE A LAWSUIT.
THEY KNOWINGLY SUBMITTED CLAIMS
FOR DOZENS OF RESEARCH GRANTS
THAT CONTAIN FALSIFIED OR
INFORMATION.
MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL SUSPENDING
LARRY BAER WITHOUT PAY THROUGH
JULY 31st.
HE WAS IN A PHYSICAL ALTERCATION
WITH HIS WIFE IN A SAN FRANCISCO
PLAZA ON MARCH FIRST
YOU ARE UP TO DATE
THAT'S THE NEWS UPDATE AT THIS
HOUR
KELLY, BACK TO YOU
>> HERE'S WHAT'S AHEAD ON THE
EXCHANGE
>> CARNIVAL HITS ROUGH WATERS.
YOUR NEXT CAR MAY BE MORE
EXPENSIVE THAN EVER.
SPIELBERG'S APPLE APPEARANCE IS
CAUSING AN UPROAR.
Each day our planet awakens
with signs of opportunity.
But with opportunity comes risk.
And to manage this risk,
the world turns to CME Group.
We help farmers lock in
future prices,
banks manage interest
rate changes
and airlines hedge fuel costs.
All so they can manage their
risks and move forward.
It's simply a matter of
following the signs.
They all lead here.
CME Group -
How the world advances.
>>> LET'S CATCH YOU UP ON A FEW
STORIES TODAY THAT SHOULD BE ON
YOUR RADAR
DOMINICK CHIU IS BACK.
LET'S TALK ABOUT PURDUE PHARMA
WHICH JUST AGREED TO A
SETTLEMENT WITH THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL OF OKLAHOMA.
THE WALL STREET JOURNAL IS
REPORTING THAT PURDUE WILL PAY
270 MILLION TO SETTLE THE FIRST
OF OVER 1600 LAWSUITS.
>> THIS IS HUGE ONLY BECAUSE OF
THE SHEER SIZE OF SETTLEMENT
NUMBER ONE
AND THEN THE NATURAL INCLINATION
IS TO TRY TO TRANSLATE THAT INTO
1600 OTHER CASES AND THERE'S NO
WAY THIS COMPANY CAN SURVIVE
THE COMPANY HAS SAID THEY HAVE
TO LOOK AT BANKRUPTCY TO PROTECT
ASSETS THERE'S NO WAY THEY CAN
PAY OUT A SETTLEMENT MORE THAN
1600 TIMES
YOU HAVE A NATIONAL STAGE FOR
OPIOD ADDICTION.
AND THIS ONE COMPANY IS THE
LIGHTNING ROD OF IT.
>> IF THAT COMPANY DOESN'T HAVE
THE RESOURCES, IS IT GOING TO GO
ELSEWHERE.
>> THE TOBACCO SETTLEMENT IN THE
'90s
THEY DO HAVE THEIR VIABLE
COMPANIES.
THEY'RE EVEN LOWER TODAY
>> HOW MUCH CAN PURDUE REALLY
AFFORD TO PAY OUT.
>> WELL, THE FAMILY THAT OWNS
PURDUE, QUITE A BIT.
>> YOU HAD PURDUE PAYING 270, OF
THAT 270, 25 MILLION OF THAT
CAME FROM THE FAMILY
FOR YEARS THEY SAID THEY WERE
PASSIVE SHAREHOLDERS IN THIS
NOW IT EMERGES FROM THE
MASSACHUSETTS CASE THAT THEY
WERE DIRECTLY INVOLVED
SO THEY COULD BE LIABLE.
THEY'RE WORTH $13 BILLION, AND
THIS IS ONLY A SMALL DROP IN THE
BUCKET AND THEIR FORTUNE IS WELL
DIVERSIFIED.
THEY'RE GOING TO FACE A LOT OF
PRESSURE PLUS NOW PEOPLE LOOKING
TO GIVE THAT MONEY BACK.
>> IS THIS A PRELUDE OF WHAT'S
TO COME?
OTHER MANUFACTURERS ARE STILL
EXPECTED TO PROCEED, INCLUDING
J & J.
>> THAT'S A GOOD POINT
LOOK AT SOME OF THE OTHERS THAT
ARE MENTIONED, THERE'S NOT A LOT
OF PRICING IN OF BILLIONS OF
DOLLARS OF THESE PAYOUTS TO BE
MADE
>> THE QUESTION IS, IS THIS A
REALTIME HANDICAPPING?
MANY OF THESE COMPANIES COULD BE
ENSNARED
IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE WALL STREET
REALLY FEELS AS THOUGH MANY OF
THESE COMPANIES THAT ARE
MENTIONED, IN BUT PERHAPS NOT AS
CLEARLY FOCUSED ON AS PURDUE ARE
GOING TO FIND SO MUCH OF THAT
FALLOUT.
THESE DAYS, PEOPLE TALK ABOUT
JOHNSTON AND JOHNSTON.
THEY'RE MORE WORRIED ABOUT BABY
POWDER.
>> THE FAMILY HAS MORE
RESOURCES.
MOVING ON TO CARNIVAL, THE
CRUISE LINE FALLING AS MUCH AS
8% TODAY
THEY DID BEAT ON EPS AND
REVENUE, BUT ISSUED WEAK
GUIDANCE
FUEL PRICES ARE GOING TO EAT
AWAY AT FUTURE EARNINGS.
THIS ON THE BACK OF THE CRUISE
INJURY
SEEN WITH THAT NORWEGIAN SHIP
THAT RAN INTO SOME PROBLEMS THIS
WEEKEND.
>> IT DID.
THE COMPANY LOWERED THEIR
GUIDANCE
CARNIVAL HAS A EUROPEAN PROBLEM,
BOOKINGS ARE UP, BUT AT LOWER
PRICING.
WHICH IS TYPICALLY NOT WHAT WALL
STREET WANTS TO SEE.
>> THAT'S A GREAT POINT, WE KNOW
IT'S IN GERMANY AND FRANCE AND
SOME OF THESE OTHER COMPANIES.
WE TALK ABOUT FRIDAY, THE BIG
SELLOFF DAY.
A LOT OF THE WEAKNESS WAS
CENTERED THERE
>> IF YOU TAKE A LOOK AT, WHEN
IT COMES TO TRAVEL AND LEISURE,
THESE ARE SOME OF THE MOST
DISCRETIONARY TYPE STOCKS.
YOU DON'T TAKE A NICE CRUISE
VACATION UNLESS YOU FEEL
COMFORTABLE ENOUGH IN YOUR
INCOME AND ABILITY TO TAKE THAT
VACATION
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING TOWARDS SOME
OF THESE HOSPITALITY COMPANIES
AS BELL WEATHERS
AND THEY'VE BEEN PRETTY GOOD UP
UNTIL NOW.
WHAT I FIND A LITTLE MORE
HEARTENING, THEY DON'T MENTION
THERE'S A DROP OFF
>> LOWER PRICING
>> AND CURRENCIES.
>> AND FUEL.
>> BE SURE TO CATCH ARNOLD
DONALD COMING UP AT 3:00 P.M
KIND OF FOLLOWING ON THIS
DISCUSSION, UP NEXT, AUTO SALES
THIS YEAR ARE EXPECTED TO FALL
BY NEARLY 5% FROM A YEAR AGO
THAT'S ACCORDING TO JD POWER
FEWER CARS ARE BEING BOUGHT.
USED CAR SALES ARE ON PACE TO
HIT THEIR HIGHEST LEVEL SINCE
THE RECESSION.
WE GET HEADLINES ALL THE TIME
NOW ABOUT SLOWDOWN IN PARTS OF
THE HOUSING MARKET, THE CAR
MARKET
THESE ARE SOME SPECIFIC PARTS,
NOT NECESSARILY THE WHOLE THING.
>> THEY SHARE BEING INTEREST
RATE SENSITIVE
WE DID SEE INTEREST RATES START
TO DECLINE A LITTLE BIT.
LIKE THE HOUSING MARKET.
YOU SAW PRICES GO UP AND UP AND
UP
IT BECAME UNAFFORDABLE FOR A LOT
OF HARD EARNING WORKERS.
PEOPLE BACKED UP AND SAID, I'M
GOING TO RENT FOR NOW.
IT'S A RESET
>> THE AVERAGE PRICE OF A
VEHICLE NOW.
OVER 33,000, YOU HAVE TO WONDER
SOME OF THESE FIRST TIME BUYERS,
IF IT'S JUST SQUEEZING OUT THAT
MARKET
>> KEVIN O'LEARY TALKED ABOUT
THIS IDEA, IF P YOU WERE A YOUNG
PERSON AGAIN, YOU WOULD ADVISE
THEM NOT TO BUY A CAR.
USE RIDE HAILING, USE LYFT AND
UBER
>> THEY'RE STILL SELLING 2.9
MILLION CARS A YEAR, RELATIVE TO
THE RECESSION LEVELS, WE'RE
STILL WAY UP FROM THERE.
IT'S FALLING DOWN A LITTLE BIT
BUT IT'S THE FIRST FALL IN A
LONG TIME.
>> IT'S ODD TO SEE WHEN YOU HAVE
A GROWING ECONOMY.
>> CRITICS WERE OUTRAGED THAT
SPIELBERG IS PUSHING APPLE'S
STREAMING SERVICE.
>> HE'S GOING TO NEED A BIGGER
PR FIRM.
>> THIS IS A LITTLE DISINGENUOUS
FOR PEOPLE TO CRITICIZE HIM.
>> HE WAS SAYING ALL STREAMING
SERVICES
HE MIGHT CONTINUE TO UPHOLD THAT
EVEN WORKING FOR APPLE
HE HASN'T SAID THAT APPLE
SHOULD, NETFLIX SHOULDN'T.
IT IS A LITTLE STRANGE FOR ONE
OF THE GREATEST FILMMAKERS OF
OUR TIME, WHO HAS LOVED THE
AWARDS TO THEN GO TO APPLE
>> YOU MAKE A DECLARATION LIKE
THAT, AND YOU'RE STEVEN
SPIELBERG, WE WANT FULL
DISCLOSURE
YOU WANT SOMETHING THAT'S
WORKING ON A NETFLIX SORT OF
COMPETITOR
>> IT SPEAKS TO THIS LANDSCAPE,
AND WHETHER FOLKS WERE
ENTRENCHED IN A CERTAIN WAY OF
DOING THINGS ARE MARRIED TO THAT
PLATFORM A LITTLE MORE
IN THIS CASE I WOULD NOT DECIDE
TO NOT WATCH OR WATCH A MOVIE
BECAUSE OF THAT PARTICULAR
COMMENT.
BUT MAYBE IT'S ONE OF THOSE
SITUATIONS WHERE FOLKS DO TEND
TO GRAVITATE MORE TOWARD CERTAIN
PLATFORMS BECAUSE OF THE
FILMMAKERS ARE INVOLVED IN
>> THEY LIKE WHAT THEY DO OR
DON'T.
I DON'T THINK MANY PEOPLE WILL
SAY, SPIELBERG IS A HACK, I'M
NOT GOING TO WATCH HIS FILMS
>>> BAD NEWS FOR PELOTON USERS
THIS IS A CRAZY STORY, THEY ARE
YANKING CLASSES THAT FEATURED
MUSIC NAMED IN A BIG PUBLISHING
LAWSUIT FILED AGAINST THE
COMPANY.
NEARLY TWO THIRDS OF THE CYCLING
CLASSES IN PELOTON'S ON DEMAND
LIBRARY ARE NOW OFFLINE.
ONE USER COMMENTED, I WANT TO
CRY.
I HAD OVER 20 BOOK MARKED RIDES
AND NOW ONLY ONE IS LEFT
I'M SO SAD
>> WHAT IS LEFT.
>> YOU GET RID OF ALL THE SONGS,
IS IT WORK OUT TO KENNY G.
OR SOMEONE YELLING AT YOU.
>> IT'S ASTOUNDING TO ME THAT
THEY DIDN'T GET THIS STUFF
APPROVED AND LICENSED BEFORE
THEY LAUNCHED.
WHAT KIND OF DEAL ARE YOU GOING
TO GET
>> YOU'RE SO SMALL -- NO ONE
REALLY CARES
>> IS THIS THE UNDER THE RADAR
TYPE OFFENSE
>> THE BUSINESS MODEL THAT WORKS
WHILE YOU'RE SMALL UNTIL YOU
HAVE TO STAND ON YOUR OWN TWO
FEET
>> UNTIL YOU'RE ABOUT TO GO
PUBLIC WITH AN $8 MILLION
VALUATION.
>> IT'S CERTAINLY NOTABLE HERE
>> HAVING A PELOTON BIKE IN YOUR
HOUSE IS A BIG INVESTMENT.
IT'S OVER $2400.
THE MONTHLY SUBSCRIPTION FEE IS
AROUND $40 A MONTH
>> THAT'S WHY THE CUSTOMERS ARE
UPSET.
PUT INVESTED A LOT OF MONEY FOR
THIS
>> MAYBE YOU SHOULD BE PAYING
$10 A MONTH.
>> PEOPLE WHO ARE BIG FANS OF
PELOTON ARE GOING TO SAY THIS IS
THE BEST THING THAT HAPPENED
SINCE JANE FONDA LEGGINGS.
>> THEY THINK PELOTON IS THE WAY
TO GO, EVEN IF THOSE CLASSES
THEY LOVED --
>> I FEEL BAD FOR SOME OF THE
INSTRUCTORS WHOSE CLASSES ARE
GONE FOREVER NOW
>> YEAH, THEY WERE TIED TO
SONGS.
FROM A NEGOTIATING POINT
THE ONLY THING THAT WAS DUMBER
TO NOT DO IT IN THE FIRST PLACE
IS TO HAVE A HUGE USER BASE
THAT'S REALLY UPSET.
>> NOW THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
PAY A LITTLE MORE.
THEY COULD HAVE TRIED TO RESOLVE
IT INSTEAD OF PAYING UP.
I'M SURPRISED THEY DIDN'T GO
THAT ROUTE
IT UNDERMINED THE WHOLE THING.
>> THAT'S MY POINT, ONCE THAT
NUMBER ONE
THEY JUST SHOULD HAVE PAID IT,
WHATEVER THAT NUMBER WAS THEY
WERE ALREADY NEGOTIATING
THEY SHOULD HAVE DONE THAT
>> THIS IS DETANTE
>> MAYBE NOT THE LEVERAGE.
>> THANK YOU ALL
>>> LYFT IS THE FIRST OF THIS
YEAR'S IPO'S THAT ARE SET TO
DEBUT ON FRIDAY.
WE'LL TAKE A LOOK AT WHY
INVESTORS HAVE SUCH AN APPETITE
FOR MONEY LOSING COMPANIES
No matter where you are in life
or what your dreams entail,
a CFP Professional is trained,
knowledgeable,
and committed to financial
planning in your best interest.
Find your CERTIFIED FINANCIAL
PLANNER™ Professional
at letsmakeaplan.org.
>>> LYFT IS EXPECTED TO GO
PUBLIC FRIDAY.
IT'S GOING TO BE THE FIRST IN A
WAVE OF START-UPS ACCORDING TO
THE WALL STREET JOURNAL THAT ARE
DEBU
DEBUTING GIANT LOSSES.
ELLIOTT, HOW UNUSUAL ARE THE
LOSSES FOR THIS YEAR'S ROUND OF
COMPANIES?
>> THEY ARE RECORD HIGH WHEN IT
COMES TO U.S. START-UPS.
$911 MILLION LAST YEAR
I THOUGHT DOT K078 WAS FULL OF
GIANT LOSSES
THIS IS THE BIGGEST 12-YEAR
LOSS -- 12-MONTH LOSS.
>> WHAT ABOUT FACEBOOK AND
GOOGLE BACK IN THE DAY BEFORE
THEY IPOED
>> BOTH OF THEM WERE RETURNING
PROFITS BY THE TIME THEY IPOED
>> IT'S ONE THING IF YOU'RE
LOSING MONEY, BECAUSE YOU'RE
GROWING SO QUICKLY
IT'S ANOTHER THING IF YOU'RE
LOSING MONEY, ALL OF A SUDDEN
HAVE YOU TO MAKE MONEY ON YOUR
OWN WITHOUT THAT
>> PART OF THE REASON THEY'VE
BEEN ABLE TO GROW SO QUICKLY
THEY ARE BURNING CASH AT THIS
POINT.
THEY'VE ALLOWED COMPANIES TO PUT
GROWTH FIRST AND PROFIT SECOND
PRIVATE INVESTORS HAVE BEEN
RECEPTIVE TO THAT.
WE'RE GOING TO GET AN INDICATION
WHETHER PUBLIC INVESTORS FEEL
THE SAME WAY
LIFT IS ABOVE THE SPECIFIC
RANGE.
WHEN IT COMES TO UBER WHICH IS
EXPECTED TO IPO IN THE NEXT
MONTH OR SO.
LOSSES OF NEARLY $2 BILLION THIS
YEAR
THIS IS ENORMOUS.
>> ELLIOTT, I WONDER, DOES LYFT,
WE COMPARE THEM WITH UBER.
DOES THAT HAVE A PATH TO
PROFITABILITY BASED ON ITS
CURRENT BUSINESS MODEL
DO THEY HAVE TO RAISE PRICES TO
GET THERE?
>> THAT IS THE QUESTION.
IT DOES NOT HAVE -- WE WILL BE
PROFITABLE BY THIS YEAR.
IT'S SORT OF UP TO THE INVESTORS
TO INFER
A LOT OF IT IS HOW MUCH DOES THE
WAR WITH UBER GO ON OVER MARKET
SHARE WHICH IS WHERE THIS IS
GOING.
>> DO COMPANIES HAVE TO MAKE
LESS ATTRACTIVE PRICING, THE ONE
THING THAT HAS DRAWN THEM SO
MANY USERS
>> I THINK THAT'S A REALLY GOOD
QUESTION
PART OF THE EQUATION IS THE
DRIVERS.
THEY'RE PROFITABLE, THEY CAN
KEEP THEIR DRIVERS AND DRIVERS
AS WE SAW YESTERDAY YOU HAD UBER
AND LYFT DRIVERS, THERE'S BEEN
SOME REGULATORY DISCUSSION
IF THEY'RE EMPLOYED AS EMPLOYEES
IN THE FUTURE, THAT'S A BIG
CHANGE
>> WHERE DOES THIS LEAVE US?
>> WE CAN COMPARE THIS TO 1999,
THAT WAS A DOT COM AND IPO
FRENZY
THEY'RE HAVING THEIR BEST
QUARTER EVER, YOU'RE SEEING
PRETTY GOOD PERFORMANCE.
WE'RE SEEING A LOT OF COMPANIES
DEBUTING
IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE IT DID BACK
THEN
DO YOU THINK INVESTORS ARE BEING
TOO KIND TO THESE COMPANIES
THINKING THEY'RE GOING TO BE THE
NEXT FACEBOOK AND GOOGLE AND NOT
REMEMBERING THAT EVEN THOSE
COMPANIES WERE PROFITABLE BY
THIS POINT
>> CERTAINLY THAT'S A LOT OF
WHAT'S DRIVING IT?
>> WE NEED TO GET INTO THE NEXT
BIG THING.
WHERE IT ENDS SORT OF LIES WITH
THE FUNDAMENTAL BUSINESS
AND HOW MUCH THEY CAN ACTUALLY
MAKE PER RIDE.
RIGHT NOW THEY LOSE MONEY ON
EVERY RIDE
>> I THINK THAT'S FOMO IN THE
MARKET NOW, YOU'VE NEVER SEEING
A RIDE SHARING COMPANY DEBUT
THIS IS SOMETHING NEW AND SHINY
FOR INVESTORS.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS THAT,
ESPECIALLY IF UBER, WHICH IS
CALLING ITSELF THE PLATFORM, A
TRANSPORTATION PLATFORM AND
DIVERSIFYING INTO SO MANY
BUSINESSES REALLY IS THE NEXT
AMAZON OR FACEBOOK
>> GREAT STUFF
APPRECIATE IT VERY MUCH.
>>> ORDERING YOUR BIG MAC AT THE
MEDICAL DONALD'S DRIVE THROUGH
COULD SOON BE EASIER
WE'LL HAVE THOSE DETAILS NEXT.
>>> PLUS, WOULD YOU KNOW WHAT TO
DO WITH YOUR FINANCES IF YOUR
LIFE WENT SIDEWAYS
COMING UP ON POWER LUNCH TODAY
ARTHUR OF THE NEW BOOK SHARES
CRUCIAL STRATEGIES FOR PREPARING
LI'S FINANCES FOR FE
UNEXPECTED MOMENTS
STAY WITH US
bank.
Capital One is
anything but typical.
That's why We designed
Capital One Cafes.
You can get savings and
checking accounts with
no fees or minimums.
AND one of America's
best savings rates.
To top it off,
you can open one from
anywhere in 5 minutes.
This isn't a typical bank.
This is Banking Reimagined.
What's in your wallet?
Hi I'm Joan Lunden.
Today's senior living
communities have never
been better,
with amazing amenities like
movie theaters, exercise rooms
and swimming pools, public
cafes, bars and bistros
even pet care services.
and there's never been
an easier way to get great
advice.
A Place for Mom is a
free service
that pairs you with a local
advisor
to help you sort through
your options
and find a perfect place.
A Place for Mom.
You know your family
We know senior living.
Together we'll make the right
choice.
>>> WELCOME BACK
McDONALD'S MAKING A BIG
ACQUISITION OF ISRAELI MARKETING
FIRM DYNAMIC YIELD
THIS IS IN HOPES OF MODERNIZING
THE DRIVE THROUGH WINDOWS.
IT'S THE BIGGEST ACQUISITION FOR
McDONALD'S SINCE BUYING BOSTON
MARKET BACK IN 1999.
KATE ROGERS WITH THE DETAILS.
>> McDONALD'S SPENDING $300
MILLION ON DYNAMIC YIELD
ACCORDING TO PEOPLE WHO ARE
FAMILIAR WITH THE DEAL
THE COMPANY USES DECISION
TECHNOLOGY TO HELP PERSONALIZE
THE CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE IN ITS
DRIVE THROUGHS
THE NEW MENU SHOWS FOOD BASED ON
THE TIME OF DAY, WHETHER CURRENT
TRAFFIC IN STORES AND EVEN
TRENDING MENU ITEMS.
THE TECH WILL USE DATA TO
INSTANTLY SUGGEST AND DISPLAY
ADDITIONAL ITEMS THAT CUSTOMERS
MIGHT LIKE BASED ON WHAT THEY'VE
JUST ORDERED
THE COMPANY TESTED THIS
TECHNOLOGY IN A FEW LOCHS ATIONS
LAST YEAR AND THEN TOP
INTERNATIONAL MARKETS.
FROM THERE, McDONALD'S WILL
INTEGRATE THE TECHNOLOGY INTO
DIGITAL EXPERIENCE TOUCH POINTS
INCLUDING KEY IKIOSKS
THE EXPERIENCE OF THE FUTURE
ROLLOUT THE STORE HAS TAKEN ON
AS IT MODERNIZES AND ADAPTS TO
CHANGING CUSTOMER PREFERENCES
AND ANALYSTS I TALKED TO
BASICALLY SAID RESTAURANT
COMPANIES KNOW THAT CUSTOMERS
MORE THAN EVER WANT THE SPEED
AND CONVENIENCE.
SOMETIMES EVEN MORE SO THAN
VALUE AND THIS IS THE REALLY
SMART MOVE FOR McDONALD'S
BECAUSE IT'S FORWARD THINKING,
KEEPS THEM VERY RELEVANT AND
MAKE THINGS EASIER AND MORE
PERSONALIZED
>> IT'S FASCINATING BECAUSE BACK
IN THE '90s, WE TALKED ABOUT
BOSTON MARKET OR THE FACT THEY
USED TO OWN CHIPOTLE, THIS IS A
NON-FAST FOOD ACQUISITION.
IT'S A MARKETING FIRM TO HELP ON
TECHNOLOGY
IT'S DIFFERENT AND FASCINATING
AND IF I'M GOING THROUGH THE
DRIVE-IN, KATE, WHAT'S LIKELY TO
CHANGE
THE MENU I'M LOOKING AT?
ARE THEY GOING TO KNOW FROM MY
LICENSE PLATE, FOR EXAMPLE, WHAT
I'VE ORDERED IN THE PAST AND
CUSTOMIZED FOR THAT?
>> MY UNDERSTANDING, THEY'LL USE
THE DATA ON WHAT YOU ORDER AND
SUGGEST THINGS YOU LIKE BUT
ITEMS THAT WORK WELL IN THE
REGION
THEY MIGHT BE POPULAR THIS,
BASED ON THE WEATHER, YOU COULD
SEE AN ICE CREAM CONE TODAY.
THEY'LL CHANGE AND ADAPT
DEPENDING ON THOSE DIFFERENT
FACTORS.
MAKE IT MORE PERSONAL FOR YOU,
PEOPLE LOVE THAT.
>> THE DRIVE-THRU IS IMPORTANT
>> CHIPOTLE IS TESTING AND
DUNKIN WITH A MOBILE ORDER ONLY
DRIVE-THRU AND IN TERMS OF
STARBUCKS, $100 MILLION INTO
RESTAURANT AND RETAIL START-UP
TECH COMPANIES THEY'RE HELPING
TO FOSTER TALENT WITH.
A LOT OF INTEREST IN THIS AREA
>> AND BY THE WAY, STARBUCKS ALL
TIME HIGH AGAIN TODAY.
KATE, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THERE'S McDONALD'S UP THREE
QUARTERS OF A PERCENT ON THIS
NEWS
>>> FEBRUARY JOBS REPORT
DISAPPOINTED BIG TIME.
WAS IT A TRUE INDICATION OF
WHAT'S PLAYING OUT IN THE LABOR
MARKET OR NOT BAD AS IT APPEARS?
LINKED IN WITH AN INSIDEOO
D LLEGE DEGREE ISN'T WHAT IT
USED TO BE
the fire going
for another 150 years.
♪♪
To inspire confidence
through style.
♪♪
I'm working to make connections
of a different kind.
♪♪
I'm working for beauty
that begins with nature.
♪♪
To treat every car
like I treat mine.
♪♪
At ADP we're designing
a better way to work,
so you can achieve
what you're working for.
♪♪
Alpha seems more
elusive today.
Is it because so many
go after it the same way,
chasing after
short-term returns?
Instead if getting
caught up with the crowd,
the investment managers at PGIM
take a long term view.
Uncovering opportunities
for alpha
across public and
private markets,
while anticipating
unforeseen risk,
has powered our rise to a
top ten
global asset manager.
Partner with PGIM.
The Global Investment Management
Businesses of
Prudential Financial, Inc.
The Global Investment Management
Businesses of
AT&T provides Edge-to-Edge
Intelligence,
covering virtually every part
of your finance business.
And so if someone tries to
breach your firewall in London
& you start to panic... don't.
Because your CTO says we've
got allies on the outside...
...& security algorithms
on the inside...
...& that way you can focus on
expanding into Eastern Europe...
...& that makes the branch
managers happy & yes, that's
the branch managers happy.
AT&T provides Edge-to-Edge
Intelligence.
It can do so much for
your business, the list
goes on and on.
That's the power of &.
& when this happens you'll
know how to quickly react...
>>> WELCOME BACK
FEBRUARY JOBS DISAPPOINTED
WE ONLY ADDED 20,000 PAYROLLS
BUT NOT BAD AS IT APPEARS.
HERE TO BREAK DOWN JOB TRENDS
AND MORE IS CAROLINA FAIRCHILD
>> THANK YOU, KELLY.
>> YOU SAW A 3% SLOWDOWN ON
HIRING FEBRUARY FROM LAST YEAR
IS THAT RIGHT?
>> THAT IS RIGHT
IT WAS THE THIRD CONSECUTIVE
MONTH WE'VE SEEN A SLOWDOWN OF
HIRING ON LINKED IN.
JOBS STILL THERE BUT EMPLOYERS
NOT HIRING THE RATE THEY WERE
BEFORE THE END OF THE YEAR.
>> ON THE DEMAND SIDE, THEY'RE
LOOKING, THE POSITIONS MIGHT BE
OPEN OR MORE, SOME THEORIES SAY
THE LABOR MARKET IS SLOWING
BECAUSE PEOPLE CAN'T FIND
QUALIFIED WORKERS TO FILL THE
POSITION.
>> THERE IS A COMPONENT HERE
WITH THE WORKFORCE NEEDING TO
ADAPT TO THE POSITIONS THAT ARE
THERE IN THE WORKFORCE RIGHT
NOW.
WE TALK ABOUT AI, AUTOMATION,
CHANGING THE JOBS THAT ARE
AVAILABLE.
WHAT WE'RE SEEING IS WORKERS
MOVE OUT OF MORE ROUTINE JOBS
INTO NON-ROUTINE JOBS THAT DON'T
REQUIRE AS MUCH TECHNOLOGY.
>> IT'S INTERESTING.
YOU SAY THEY'RE REPETITIVE DESK
JOBS AND THOSE ON THE DECLINE
BECAUSE OF TECHNOLOGY.
>> THAT IS CORRECT
SO THESE WORKERS ARE SEEING A
DECLINE IN JOBS AND PROVIDING
MORE FLEXIBILITY AND HIGHER PAY.
A LOT OF MYTHS OF PEOPLE WITHOUT
COLLEGE DEGREE NOT SEEING ENOUGH
JOB OPPORTUNITIES BUT THERE ARE
A LOT FOR NON-ROUTINE WORK
ELECTRICIANS, PLUMBERS, DRIVERS.
>> CONSTRUCTION, HEALTH CARE,
ALL NON-ROUTINE AND THE GROWTH,
HOW MUCH GROWTH ARE WE TALKING
ABOUT?
AND SO THESE ARE JOBS THAT
BASICALLY ANYBODY COULD FILL
>> THE GROWTH WE'RE SEEING IN
NON-ROUTINE JOBS IS LIKE
MIMICKING SOME OF THE DECLINE IN
NON-ROUTINE.
4% GROWTH THAT'S MIMICKING 3%
DECLINE.
>> OKAY, THAT'S HAPPENING
UNDERNEATH THE SURFACE
I'M CURIOUS GOING BACK TO THIS
OVERALL NUMBER HERE ABOUT THE
HIRING SLOWING DOWN.
ANYTHING MORE YOU CAN TELL US
ANECDOTALLY WHY COMPANIES MIGHT
BE SLOWING UP A BIT?
>> I THINK WHAT WE SEE ON LINKED
IN IS EMPLOYEES BEEFING UP THEIR
PROFILES TO BE MORE ATTRACTIVE
TO EMPLOYERS
PERHAPS TAKE CLASSES ON LINKEDIN
LEARNING TO BE MORE ATTRACTIVE
FOR THE JOBS BECOMING FEWER AND
FEWER.
>> IT IS INTERESTING THAT, YOU
KNOW, BECAUSE THE PAYROLL
ITSELF, 20,000, THAT WAS A
SLOWDOWN, BUT THE WAGE NUMBER IN
THERE WAS VERY GOOD.
THE UNEMPLOYMENT RATE COMES FROM
DIFFERENT SURVEYS, VERY GOOD
THE SHARE OF PEOPLE IN THE LABOR
FORCE, A LOT OF POSITIVE TRENDS
AND I WONDER, IS THE SLOWDOWN
REFLECTING SOMETHING IN WEATHER
LITERALLY OR TRADE ISSUES AND
PARTS OF THE ECONOMY ARE
SLOWING.
>> THERE IS SOME OF THAT GOING
ON AND SEE AN UPTICK AFTER THE
SHUTDOWN IN SOME OF THE SECTORS
WHERE THERE WAS MORE OF A
SLOWDOWN BECAUSE OF THE
SHUTDOWN
WE'RE SEEING MORE PLAYERS PICK
UP THOSE JOBS.
>> MEGAN, QUICKLY FOR YOU, FROM
MIKE IN NEW YORK CITY, HOM IT'S
RATHER THAN HAVING IT DOWN
LOADED AUTOMATICALLY.
>> AND YOU JUST MAKE THE
ANNOUNCEMENT AS YOU POINTED OUT
THAT'S VERY IMPORTANT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, SIR.
YOU CAN FOLLOW ME ON FACEBOOK
AND TWITTER OR TWEET THE SHOW AT
THE LEAD CNN AND OUR COVERAGE ON
CNN CONTINUES RIGHT■  NOW.
>> CHARGED WITH LYING TO POLICE.
I'LL TALK TO CALLING IT A WHITE
WASH.
GREAT REPORT AFTER MONTHS OF
TOSSING AROUND PHRASES LIKE
WITCH HUNT AND HOAX PRESIDENT
TRUMP CALLS ROBERT MUELLER'S
REPORT GREAT.
HE FALSELY CLAIMS IT EXONE
GIULIANI IS HERE IN THE
SITUATION ROOM LIVE.
WE PEEL AND REPEAL AS THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION TO A ELIMINATE
THE ACT.
WHY DEMOCRATS FEEM THEY HAVE A
NEW WEAPON.
IS IT A MESSAGE TO NORTH KOREA?
I'M WOLF OF BLITZER.
YOU'RE IN THE■■■ SITUATION ROOM.
>>> THEY FURIOUS WHO CALLS IT A
WHITE WASH OF JUSTICE.
ALSO AS THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
SAYS IT WILL TAKE WEEKS TO
RELEASE THE MUELLER REPORT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SEIZES TO
DECLARE VICTORY WHILE FALSELY
CLAIMING THAT THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL EXONERATED HIM OF
OBSTRUCTION.
THE PRESIDENT IS USING MUELLER'S
FINDINGS TO ATTACK CRITICS.
IT MAY HAVE JUST GIVEN DEMOCRATS
A 2020 BATTLE CRY WITH A NEW
EFFORT TO GET RID OF OBAMACARE.
RUDY GIULIANI IS STANDING BY.
LET'S BEGIN WITH TODAY'S
SHOCKING DEVELOPMENTS IN THE
SMOLLETT CASE.
SO HOW IS EVERYONE EXPLAINING
THIS EXTRAORDINARY TURN OF
EVENTS.
>> RIGHT NOW THEY ARE NOT.
IT HAS BEEN AHEAD SKRAFRPING
FROM THE PUBLIC TO THE MAYOR'S
OFFICER.
PEOPLE WANT TO KNOW HOW HE ENDED
UP HERE.
THE JUDGE HAS SEALED THIS CASE.
HT CHICAGO OFFICIALS FUR■
USE.
FURIOUS.
>> WHERE DO I THINK JUSTICE IS
THIS?
I THINK THIS CITY IS STILL
AN APOLOGY.
>> ALL CHARGES WERE DROPPED
AFTER HE WAS ACCUSED OF STAGING
AN ATTACK TO LOOK LIKE A HATE
CRIME.
>> WE FOUND OUT ABOUT WHEN YOU
ALL DID.
>> OFFICIALS CLAIMING THAT IT
WAS A HOAX.
THE STATE SEALING ALL OF THE
EVIDENCE IN THE CASE.
>> CLOSE TO HIDE BEHIND SECRECY
AND BROKER A DEAL.
MY DEAL IS TOTIGATE AN
INCIDENT, GATHER EVIDENCE AND
GATHER FACTS AND PRESENT THEM TO
THAT'S WHAT WE DID.
I STAND BEHIND THE
INVESTIGATION.
>> TODAY SMOLLETT TOOK A VICTORY
LAP AT THE COURTHOUSE.
>> I HAVE BEEN TRUTHFUL ON EVERY
LEVEL SINCE DAY ONE.
I WOULD NOT BE MY MOTHER'S SON
I WAS CAPABLE OF ONE DROP
THAT I'M ACCUSED OF.
>> KEEPING IN MIND RESOURCES IS
TO COMBAT VIOLENT CRIME AND THE
DRIVERS OF VIOLENCE.
THE DECISIONED TO■÷ OFFER
THIS DISPOSITION IN THE CASE.
>> HIS LAWYERS EARLIER POINTING
FINGERS AT CHICAGO POLICE.
>> WE HAVE NOTHING TO SAY TO THE
POLICE DEPARTMENT EXCEPT TO
INVESTIGATE CHARGE AND NOT TRY
THEIR CASES IN THE PRESS TO
BRING CHARGES AND TO0] JUMP
AHEAD AND UTILIZE THE PRESS TO
CONVICT PEOPLE BEFORE THEY ARE
TRIED IN A COURT OF LAW.
>> QUITE FRANKLIN IT EVERYBODY
OFF.
>> STRONG WORDS BY
SUPERINTENDENT ANNOUNCING
CHARGES AGAINST SMOLLETT.
>> AND WHY THIS STUNT WAS ORK
STRAITED BECAUSE HE WAS DITS
DISSATISFIED ABOUT HIS SALARY.
>> CHICAGO'S MAYOR.
>> NOT ONLY IS IT $10,000 BUT
ALL OF THE OTHER REPERCUSSIONS
IT MADE TO ME, WHERE IS THE
ACCOUNTABILITY OF THE SYSTEM?
YOU CANNOT HAVE BECAUSE OF A
PERSON'S POSITION ONE SET OF
RULES APPLY TO THEM AND ANOTHER
SET OF RULES APPLY TO EVERYBODY
ELSE.
>> WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT THIS IT
GOT INTERNATIONAL ATTENTION.
I'M TOLD THOSE TWO MEN HAVE THE
TEXT MESSAGE EXCHANGES BETWEEN
SMOLLETT AND THEMSELVES SO THEY
A LOT OF QUESTIONS WITH THIS.
NOW THAT IT'S SEALED WE PLAY
NEVER KNOW WHAT POLICE ACTUALLY
HAD.
>> THIS IS RYAN YOUNG FOR US.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON THIS BREAKING
NEWS COMING UP LATER IN THE
SITUATION ROOM.
I'LL SPEAK LATER WITH HIM.
OTHER BIG STORIES INCLUDING
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HE IS NOW GOING ON THE OFFENSIVE
IN THE WAKE OF A MUELLER REPORT
AT LEAST THE SUMMARY THAT IS
RELEASED.
HI■■ID■■■■■O■O W■■■■        ■■■k
■■■SEL FOUND HE DID N ENGAGE O■■
IN ■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
■■P■■■■■■■■■■■PT
A CLEAR HEALTH CARE PLAN OF ITS
OWN.
SOAK IN THE FINDINGSO OF
ROBERT MUELLER'S REPORT HE
DIDN'T STICK TO THE FACTS.
>> THE MUELLER REPORT WAS GREAT.
IT COULD NOT HAVE BEEN BETTER.
IT SAID NO OBSTRUCTION, NO
COLLUSION.
IT COULD NOT HAVE BEEN BETTER.
>> BUT THAT'S NOT TRUE.
WHILE ATTORNEY GENERAL SUMMARY
DID STATE THAT THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL FOUND THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN
DID NOT CONSPIRE THE QUESTION OF
OBSTRUCTION WAS LEFT TO THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT AND IT WAS
BAR AND DEPUTY ATTORNEYERAL
WHO DECIDED NOT TO PROSECUTE.■#
PRESIDENT'S WORD FOR IT AND
DEMANDING TO SEE THE FULL
REPORT.
THEY DON'T NEED AN
INTERPRETATION BY AN ATTORNEY
GENERAL APOINTED FOR A
PARTICULAR JOB TO MAKE SURE THE
PRESIDENT IS WE NEED TO SEE THE
REPORT.
>> PRESIDENT ALSO ACCUSED
UNSPECIFIED FORCES OF
CONSPIREING AGAINST HIM.
>> WE CANNOT LET IT EVER HAPPEN
AGAIN.
IT WENT VERY HIGH UP AND IT
STARTED FAIRLY LOW BUT WITH
INSTRUCTIONS FROM THE HIGHP
THIS SHOULD NEVER HAPPEN TO A
PRESIDENT AGAIN.
WE ISN'T ALLOW THAT TO TAKE
PLACE.
>> MR. TRUMP ACCUSED THE OBAMA
WARE WHITE HOUSE OF SWIER
TAPPING HIM.
ONE OF THE PRESIDENT'S TOP ALLY
SAYS HE URGED TO GIVE THE
DOSSIER TO THE FBI.
>> HE CALLED ME UP AND SAID WHAT
DO YOU THINK?
SHOULD I TURN IT OVER TO THE
FBI?
I SAID YES.
>> ONE AREA THERE IS AGREEMENT
IMPEACHMENT AGREES TO BE OFF THE
TABLE.
>> IT IS NOT OFF OF THE TABLE
UNTIL IN THE TABLE.
>>.
>> THE FEDERAL JUNL'S RULING
SAYING IN A STIMT THE COMP HEN
IFR AGREEMENT.
HE JUMPED IN AND DID DAMAGE
CONTROL.
>> THE REPUBLICAN PARTY WILL
SOON BE KNOWN ADDS THE PARTY OF
HEALTH CARE.
YOU WATCH.
>> HE VOWED TO TAKE CARE OF
PEOPLE WITH PREEXISTING
CONDITIONS.
PROTECTIONS. OBAMACARE'S KEY
>> I WILL ALWAYS FIGHT FOR AND
ALWAYS PROTECT PATIENTS WITH
>> AFTERy■[X■■■■ú PROTECTING
OBAMACARE IN THE MIDTERMS
DETERD
DEMOCRATS ARE MORE THAN READY.
>> IT T A■■■■■■ TWO-YEAR ANCHOR
■■■■ THE NA■A■AsAsA■■s■sA■■■EAS.
CONFIRMED TO IS ATTORNEY IS
@;@;@;@; PARDON THE ■■■s■sIDENT.
HE TOLD CNN IQ■■■@■■Q■■■■■■■■■■
WOULD ■■■■■■Q■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■.
THIDENT HAQ■Q■Q■■■■■         SU.
HE HAS TOLD REPORTERS HE HASN'T
GIVEN IT A LOT OF THOUGHT YET.
>> THANKS VERY MUCH.
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S PERSONAL TONE
GIULIANI, THE FORMER MAYOR OF
THANKS FOR COMING IN.
>> NICE TO BE HERE.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL'S SUMMARY.
DO YOU HAVE A COPY OVER THERE?
>> I'M READY.
>> THE PRESIDENT IS NOW SAYING
THAT THE MUELLER REPORT IN HIS
WORD IS GREAT AND THAT ROBERT
MUELLER WHO SPENT NEARLWO
YEARS INVESTIGATING ALL OF THIS
ACTED HONORABLY.
DO YOU AGREE WITH THE PRESIDENT?
>> N THAT HE ACTED ON HONORABLY.
>> TELL US WHY YOU WOULD HAVE TO
DISAGREE.
>> WE HAVE HAD -- YOU KNOW,
PEOPLE SEE IT DIFFERENTLY.
MAYBE I WAS IN THE TRENCHES
MORE.
I THOUGHT THAT TREATMENT OF
MANAFORT WAS WAY OVER THE TOP.
IT THINK IT SHOULDN'T BE
ALLOWED.
THEY SHOULD TAKE THEM, PUT THEM
IN SOLITARYONFINEMENT
BASICALLY TELLING THEM WHAT YOU
>/LY. THEY LYINGUT.>]O SAYING H■
■=■=■=■■■■■■■■
PARDONS.
I HAVE TAKEN THE SAME POSITION
FROM DAY ONE UNTIL NOW.
>> HE WAS TREATED THERE ALMOST A
GROSSLY HORRIBLE WAY.
>> AND YOU PLEADED GUILTY.
>> YEAH BUT HE NEVER SAID WHAT
THEY WANTED HIM TO SAY.
HE GOT THAT BIG LONG SENTENCE.
>> HE IS ABOUT TO GO TO JAIL FOR
SEVEN AND A HALF YEAR.
>> I'M NOT SAYING HE IS
BLAMELESS.
I'M TELLING YOU, HE WAS TREATED
HORRIBLY.
HE WAS TREATED I A WAY THAT'S
VERY VERY DANGEROUS.
A PROSECUTOR COMES VERY CLOSELY
TO THAT.
YOU PUT A CERTAIN AMOUNT OF
PRESSURE ON SOMEBODY.
THAT'S POINT AT WHICH YOU KNOW
I'M PUTTING TOO MUCH PRESSURE
ON.
MAY GHAT I WANT TO HEAR
BUT IT MAY NOT BE TRUE.
>> IF SOMEBODY WAS STEALING
MILLIONS AND MILLIONS OF DOLLARS
NOT FILING TAX RETURNS THE WAY
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO FILE,
WOULDN'T YOU GO AFTER THAT
INDIVIDUAL?
>> OF COURSE WE WOULD.
>> OF COURSE I WOULD.
I WOULDN'T RAID HIS HOUSE.
I WOULD NOT PUT HIM IN SOLITARY
CONFINEMENT.
THAT'S CRAZY.
MOST TERRORISTS AREN'T IN
SOLITARY CONFINEMENT.
>> LET ME ASK YOU THIS --
>> MAY I FINISH THE SENTENCE YOU
TO LET ME FINISH THE SENTENCE.
>> POWELL WROTE A BOOK CALLED --
I HAVE FORGOT THE NAME OF THE
BOOK BUT IT'S A BOOK ABOUT ABUSE
OF POWER.
>> HE WAS ONE OF THE PROSECUTORS
WORKING.
>> HE WAS HANDLING THE MANAFORT
CASE.
13 TIMES BACK AND FORTH THE GUY
WAS IN SOLITARY.
THEY CONTENDED THAT HE KNEW THAT
THE PRESIDENT DID NOT HAVE
MEETING WITH THAT RUSSIAN WOMAN.
>> AND HE CONTENDED HE DID NOT?
>> YES.
EACH TIME THEY WOULD SAY YOU'RE
LIE, YOU'RE LYING, YOU'RE LYING.
WE HAPPEN TO HAVE THAT MATERIAL
SENT TO US.
IT WAS KIND OF A BIG DEAL AT THE
TIME THAT IT■= HAPPENED.
>> IN HIS LETTER I HAVE A COPY
THAT HE DID INTERFERE IN THE
U.S. PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION IN
2016.
>> YOU NEVER DISCUSSED THAT?
>> THE PRESIDENT DOESN'T
DISAGREE RUSSIANS INTERFERED.
WHAT HE DISAGREED WITH IS THAT
HE HAD ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT.
>> LISTEN TO WHAT THE PRESIDENT
SAID AFTER HE MET WITH, YOU
KNOW, WITH THE RUSSIAN LOOET
LEADER.
>> IT IS KIND OF SWITCHING.
>> THE HEADLINE HERE IS --
>> HOLD ON A SECOND.
>> AFTER TWO YEARS OF SAYING
COLLUSION, COLLUSION, COLLUSION
ON THIS NETWORK THE WHOLE
PURPOSE OF MUELLER'S.
>> OF COURSE HE■> WAS.
SIT THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT'S
EFFORTS TO INTERFERE IN THE 2016
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION.
THEY INVESTIGATED THAT.
THEY CONFIRMED THAT.
IT'S IN THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
SUMMARY OF THE MUELLER REPORT.
IT INTRIGUED ME WHY THE
PRESIDENT MAYBE REFUSES TO STILL
ACCEPT THAT.
LISTEN TO WHAT HE SAID.
LISTEN TO THIS.
I HAVE PRESIDENT PUTIN.
HE SAID IT'S NOT RUSSIA.
I WILL SAY THIS, I DON SEE ANY
REASON WHY IOULD BE.
>> I MEAN THAT'S CLE THE
WHOLE OBJECTIVE WHILE THE
RUSSIANS INTERFERED IN THE
PRESIDENT SHLG ELECTION.
THE U.S. INTELLIGENCE CONCLUDED
THEY HAD THREE GOALS.
TO HARM ELECT BLT, HELP DONALD
TRUMP'S ELECTION CHANCE AND
UNDER DPTS MINE.
WHY WON'T THE PRESIDENT ACCEPT
WHAT HIS OWN INTELLIGENCE TELLS
HIM?
>> HE SAYS THIS IS A VERY GOOD
REPORT AND I AGREE IT IS A VERY
VERY GOOD SUMMARY I HAVE NO
REASON TO BELIEVE IT.
HE READ IT.
HE DIDN'T OBJECT TO IT.
IENT OVER THIS LETTER IN GREAT
DETAIL.
THE ONLY THING WE HAVE ANY ISSUE
WITH IS THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
PUNTING THE DECISION ON
OBSTRUCTION TO THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL.
I THINK HE SHOULD HAVE MADE THAT
DECISION.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE AGREE WITH
YOU ON THAT.
HE SHOULD HAVE MADE A SPECIFIC
RECOMMENDATION.
>> ALSO, REMEMBER, THIS ALSO
DOES NOTRATE HIM.
>> I WILL GET TO THAT IN A
MOMENT.
>> THAT'S KIND OF CLOSE TO AN
IMPROPER STATEMENT.
>> THE ATTORNEY GENERAL IN HIS
LETTER, THE FOUR-PAGE LETTER
QUOTES MUELLER AS SAYING THAT
THE INVESTIGATION I'M QUOTING
FROM THE LETTER DID NOT
ESTABLISH THAT MEMBER OF THE
TRUMP CAMPAIGN COORDINATED WITH
THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT.
SO IS THERE AN INNOCENT
EXPLANATION WHY SO MANY TRUMP
ASSOCIATES WERE MEETING WITH
RUSSIANS DURING THE CAMPA
>> IT WASN'T THATR MANY -- HE
PLEADED GUILTY.
HI LIED ABOUT INTERACTIONS WHO
HAD TIES TO RUSSIAN
INTELLIGENCE.
ALL OF THESE PEOPLE LIED ABOUT
RUSSIAN CONTEXT.
NONE OF THEM WENT TO THE FBI AND
REPORTED THE CONTEXT OF THE FBI.
>> AT THE TIME THAT IT■ HAPPENE.
>> TIME OUT.
>> ISN'T THAT SOMETHING YOU
SHOULD TELL THE DPRFBI ABOUT?
>> IF YOU BELIEVE IT WAS ABOUT
SANCTIONS, RIGHT AND HE FAILED
TO DISCLOSE THAT AND HE MISLEAD
THE VICE PRESIDENT.
IT HAD NOTHING TOITH■
INFORM ON?=?m HILLARY.
SO IT TOOK PLACE AFTER THE
ELECTION.
SO WHETHER HE TOLD THE TRUTH OR
DIDN'T TELL THE TRUTH GOT
NOTHING TO DO WITH?■LUSION.
SO ONCE AGAIN MULTIPLE OFFERS TO
ASSIST THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN DOES
IT REGRET THAT HIS ASSOCIATES
AFTER GETTING THOSE OFFERS NEVER
REPORTED THOSE CONTACTS TO THE
FBI.
>> I CAN'T SAY WHETHER HE DOES
ORC DOESN'T.
YOU SAY WE HAVE INFORMATION THAT
IS DAMAGING TO HILLARY CLINTON.
THERE IS INFORMATION THAT WILL
HELP DONALD TRUMP SHOULDN'T THEY
NOTIFY THE FBI OF THAT?
>> I WOULD SAY WHAT YOU'RE DOING
IS MISSING THE FOREST THROUGH
THE TREES.
SPECIAL COUNSEL DID NOT --
>> BUT --
>> LET ME READ IT.
>> DID IN THE CONSPIRE DESPITE
MULTIPLE EFFORTS --
>> I AGREE.
>> THAT'S THE HEADLINE.
>> THE HEADLINE THEY DID NOT
CONSPIRE OR KOOR DIN FLAT.
THE QUESTION IS WHAT ABOUT ALL
OF THE MULTIPLE EFFORTS BY
RUSSIAN OFFICIALS TO TRY TO MEET
WITH THESE --
>> I GUESS THEY ANTICIPATED WHAT
IS GOING TO HAPPEN OR HAVE
DETAILED KNOWLEDGE OF THE LAW.
>> WHAT YOULD HAVE DONE IF
DURING THE CAMPAIGN AND YOU
WERE --
>> I HAPPENED TO BE A LAWYER.
>> WHAT YOULD WOULD YOU DONE IF
A RUSSIAN SAID I WILL HELP
THE -- WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE DONE?
>> I WOULD HAVE REPORTEDER
BECAUSE I KNEW IT COULD BE A
VIOLATION OF THE LAW.
IT GETS YOU INTO A WHOLE
DISCUSSION OF IS IT A CAMPAIGN
CONTRIBUTION OR NOT?
OUT OF AN EXCESS OF CAUTION, IF
YOU CAME TO ME OR SOMEBODY ON
THE CAMPAIGN CAME TO ME AND SAID
ASIAN OFFICIAL OFFERED
DIFFERENTY INFORMATION ON
HILLARY, NOW, YOU DON'T STRICTLY
HAVE TO DO IT.
NOTHING ILLEGAL ABOUT REPORTING
A CRIME.
NUMBER TWO, THIS IS ARGUABLY A
CRIME.
A BIG DEBATE AS TO WHETHER OR
NOT INFORMATION FROM A FOREIGNER
IS A CONTRIBUTION TO THE
CAMPAIGN.
SOME LAWYERS SAY YES.
SOME LAW;b;&AY NO.
THE VUE OF IT?
DOES IT HAVE A MONETARY VALUE?
HELL OF A RUSH.
NO STRICT DUTY TO REPORT.
I GUARANTEE YOU MOST OF THESE
PEOPLE VA HEARD ME, THEY
WOULDN'T HAVE KNOWN IT'S A
VIOLATION OF THE LAW.
THEY WOULD HAVE HAD NO IDEA THAT
A FREFRM PERSON SAYS I GOT DIRTY
INFORMATION ON TRUMP OR HILLARY
THAT IS IT A POSSIBLE VIOLATION
OF THE LAW.
PLEASE, I REALLY BELIEVE IT IS A
SMALL POINT IN LIKE OF THE FACT
THAT FOR TWO NAR YEARS HE LIED.
>> LET'S GET TO THE ISSUE OF
ZBLP IT BEGAN BECAUSISH SHA WAS
TRYING TO BER HE SAID RUSSIANS
HAD INFORMATION.
>> MAP IT WILL TURN OUT.
IT MAY NOT BE CORRECT.
>> DO YOU BETTER INFORMATION?
>> I DO BUT I'M NOT AT LYNNERTY
TO KIS THOSE IT LAST NIGHT.
IT WAS THE US A TRAIL DWRANS
THAT WED.
I HAVE NO KNOWLEDGE OF ANY
HACKING M IT IS LEFT OAT TO BE
DFRP HE WROTE AN EXPERT REPORT
ON RUSSIA.
HADN'T BEEN THERE FOR NINE
YEARS.
NOBODY TOLD THE JUDGE HE GOT
FIRED.
FLOEB TOLD ANYBODY AT THE
DOSSIER SHE PAID $1.1 MILLION TO
HAVE IT.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS.
HE SAYS THIS REPORT BASED ON THE
SUMMARY ALL OF US HAVE READ IS A
COMPLETE AND TOTAL EXONERATION.
THIS IS WHAT THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL QUOTES MUELLER AS SAYING
WHILE IT DOES NOT CONCLUDE IT
ALSO DOES NOT EXONERATE.
IS THE PRESIDENT FRUSTRATED BY
THAT ONE LINE QUOTED IN THIS
DOCUMENT?
>> NO.
I THINK THE PRESIDENT IS SAYING
YOU READ THIS LETTER AND NEXT
PARAGRAPH OF THE LETTER RIGHT
AFTER THIS THIS DECISION ABOUT
IS IT A CRIME OR IS IT ANOTHER
CRIME WAS TO THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL TO ROSEN STEIN.
I UNDERSTAND ALTHOUGH I DON'T
HAVE DETAILED KNOWLEDGE OF THIS
THEY TOOK TWO TO THREE WEEKS.
>> THREE WEEKS.
>> THAT'S ABOUT RIGHT THEY GAVE
IT TO --
>> OFF OF THE LEGAL COUNSEL OR
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT.
THEY REVIEWED EVERY CASE ON
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE AND CAME
TO THIS CONCLUSION.
IT EXONERATES IT.
I GUESS YOU WOULD HAVE TO SAY
MUELLER AND BAR EXONERATED HIM
ON COLLUSION AND THE ATTY
OBSTRUCTION NOT MUELLER.
MUELLER I CAN'T SAY IT'S A
CRIME BUT I CAN'T EXONERATE.
THIS IS ABOUT AS GOOD AS A
DECLINATION.
>> THEY SAID HE IS ON HONORABLE
GUY.
MAYBE THE GUY WAS CONFUSED AND
HE PUNTED HIM.
I HAVE A GUESS AS TO WHAT
HAPPENED.
I THINK HIS STAFF WAS AND AS A
QUESTION.
>> BUT YOU KNOW ROBERT MUELLER.
>> YES.
>> AND I SIDE FROM THE CRITICISM
I GAVE YOU BEFORE I HAVE A GOOD
VIEW OF HIM.
EVERYBODY MAKES MISTAKES.
>> HE WOULDN'T MAKE UP HIS OWN
MIND?
>> HE SAYS -- I MEAN I IMAGINE
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL DESCRIBED
WHAT THE SPECIAL COUNCIL VIEWS
AS.HERS SUGGESTED HE WAS TO
DECIDE WHETHER THE PRESIDENT DID
ANYTHING.
>> HE STILL GOT A LAWYER NOT
REALIZED IT WAS THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL'S POSITION.
SO HE DIDN'T ACTUALLY CHARGE IT
FROM THE ATTORNEY GENERAL.
ALSO FROM THE IDEA HE REPORTED
IT THREE WEEKS EARLIER I THINK
HE NIGH THAT IT WOULD BE A
REVIEW.
>> YOU DON'T FLOW FOR SURE THAT
MUELLER WANTED THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL TO MAKE A FINAL
DECISION.
I DO THINK HE WOULD NOT HAVE
REPORTED THREE WEEKS EAR
>> YOU W THIS WHOLE MUELLER
REPORT TO BE RELEASED WITH THE
EXCLUSION OF SOME GRAND JURY
TESTIMONY OR NATIONAL SECURITY
SECRETS CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
YOU WANT IT TO BE RELEASED WHEN?
>> CONSISTENT WITH THE LAW
KNOWING HOW LONG IT IS REPORTED
TO BE.
>> AND IF THEY WANT TO PUT OUT
GRAND JURY MATERIAL THEY CAN GO
TO A JUDGE AND GET IT.
THEY MIGHT NOT GET IT BUT THEY
CAN TRTO DO IT.
>> IF THE PRESIDENT HAD NOTHING
TO HIDE WHY WEREN'T YOU WILLING
TO LETIM SIT DOWN FOR AN
INTERVIEW SPECIAL COUNS>■■■■■>■
WRITING BUT HE NEVER AGREED TO
SIT DOWN AND TALK ABOUT IT.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GET SUED FOR
MALPRACTICE.
I WOULD BE A HELD OF AN AWFUL
LAWYER IF I WALKED HIM IN WHERE
I HAD EVERY REASON TO BELIEVE
THEY WEREN'T IN GOOD FAITH.
THEY WERE GOING TO TRY TO TRAP
HIM WITH COHEN LYING HIS WHAT
OFF.
I'M NOT ARGUING HE THE
TRUTH OR DIDN'T TELL HIM.
TH?I?I TRAPP?I■I■I■I HIM.
THEY HAD EVERYTHING.
THEY ASKED HIM DID YOU HAVE ANY
MEETI
MEETINGS.
THEY ASKED THE QUESTION.
HE SAID I DON'T REMEMBER A
MEETING LIKE THAT.
IF YOU DO THAT YOU TAKE THE MEMO
OUT AND YOU SAY LOOK, YOU HAD A
MEETING.
DOES THAT REFRESH YOUR
RECKLATR
RECOLLECTION ABOUT THAT MEETING?
YOU KEEP IT IN THE DESK.
WHEN IT COMES NEXT TO THAT YOU
SAY PERJURY.
WE ALSO KNOW SOME OF THE FBI
AGENTS DIDN'T THINK HE LIED
ABOUT IT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW IT ALL SWITCHED
INTO CHARGING IT.
>> I TAKE IT IN THE Q AND A YOU
DIDN'T WANT THE PRESIDENT TO
ANSWER ANY QUESTIONS INVOLVING
OBSTRUCTION, IS THAT RIGHT?
>> A COUPLE REASONS FOR THAT.
NUMBER ONE THE PRIVILEGE THAT HE
HAS, THE EXECUTIVE PREF LIJ THAT
HE HAS IS MUCH STRONGER FROM THE
DAY HE IS ELECTED PRESIDENT.
SO JUST CONVENIENTLY DIVIDED
INTO THE COLLUSION, ALLEGED
COLLUSN ALL TOOK PLACE BEFORE
HE WAS PRESIDENT.
>> A PRIVATE CITIZEN.
>> WE COULD HAVE MADE A CLAIM OF
PRIVILEGE.
OUR CHANCESO OF WINNING THAT
WOULD BE BETTER THAN OURS.
TON OTHER HAND FROM THE DAY HE
BECOMES PRESIDENT AND THE DAY HE
IS INAUGURATED IT BECOMES VERY
STRONG.
HE DOESN'T ONLY BECOME STRONG IT
IS BECAUSE OF WHAT THEY DID.
BY TURNING OVER 1.4 MILLION
DOCUMENTS BY NOT OBJECTING TO 50
WITNESSES, REMEMBER BILL CLINTON
OBJECTED TO WITNESSES MADE IT
HARDER FOR HIM TO ASSERT
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE.
HE GOT INDICTED FOR PERJURY.
THEY SAT HIM DOWN FOR AN
INTERVIEW.
IT IS KIND OF ON OUR MIND.
SO I'M A LAWYER.
I'M NOT A POLITICIAN.
I AM A POLITICIAN.
IN THIS ROLE I'M A LAWYER.
MY JOB IS TO PROTECT MY CLIENT.
IF HE WEREN'T THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES THERE WOULD BE
NO CONSIDERATION AT ALL.
MOST PEOPLE UNDER INVESTIGATION
DO NOT GO INTO A GRAND JURY OR
TESTIFY UNDER OATH.
EVERY ONE I MADE I DIDN'T HAVE
THE BENEFIT.
>> AND YOU CAN RELAEASE ON YOUR
OWN Q AND A WHAT HE DID WITH
MUELLER.
>> WHEN YOU RELEASE IT ASSUMING
THEY DON'T WANT TO RELEASE IT DO
YOU A PROBLEM RELEASING THAT?
>> THE ANSWERS ARE ALL TRUTHFUL
OTHERWISE YOU WOULD HAVE SEEN
IT.
>> WE WOULD LOVE TO HAVE SEEN
WHAT THE SPECIAL COUNSEL ASKS
AND WHAT THE PRESIDENT SAID.
I ASSUME YOU WORKED REALLY HARD
TO WRITE THE ANSWERS.
>> HE GAVE THE ANSWERS AND WE
WORKED REALLY HARD TO MAKE SURE
HIS RECOLLECTION WAS CORRECT.
YOU LOOKED AT THE DOCUMENTS YOU
HAVE TO LOOK AT WHICH WOULDN'T
HAVE HAPPENED IN A SITUATION
WHERE THEY ARE TRYING TO TRAP
IT.
>> AND SO YOU CAN ASSURE US?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> BUT UP TO YOU YOU WOULD
RELEASE IT?
>> NOTHING IN THERE I HAVE ANY
PROBLEM WITH.
I THINK YOU KNOW MOST OF THE
ANSWERS THAT ARE IN THERE.
>> WE WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED SM.
>> NO SURPRISE.
>> HOW MANY PAGES WAS IT?
>> THE QUESTIONS WERE ABOUT
RECOLLECTION NOW BACK THEN SEVEN
OR EIGHT PAGES OF QUESTIONS.
THEY HAD A TOPIC AND THEN HAD
EIGHT SUB QUESTIONS.
THEN OUR ANSWERS THEN GO IN
SEQUENCE WITH THOSE.
SO MAYBE OUR WE VENN CLUL
ANSWERS AT 15O 20 PAGES.
>> YOU TOLD MY COLLEAGUE YOU
HAVE A 97 PAGE REBUTTAL READY TO
BE RELEASED.
>> 87.
>> CAN YOU GIVE US A SENSE OF
WHAT IS THERE T REPORT?
>> YEAH.
LET'S TALK ABOUT OBSTRUCTION.
IT GOES ON -- IT GOES INTO WHY
THIS COULD NOT BE AN OBSTRUCTION
ON MANY DIFFERENT LEVELS.
ONE OF THE THINGS THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL PICKS UP ON THERE WAS NO
UNDERLYING CRIME BY EXONERATING
HIM ON COLLUSION IT TURNS OUT
THEY ARE NOT --
>> PEOPLE GO TO JAIL EVEN THOUGH
THEY DIDN'T COMMIT A CRIME.
>> YOU LIED ABOUT IT.
>> THE ATTORNEY GENERAL SAYS IT
IS HARD TO FIND INTENT.
YOU CAN.
>> SHE DIDN'T ENGAGE THERE
INSIDER TRADING BUT SHE WOUND UP
IN JAIL BECAUSE SHE LIED ABOUT
IT.
>> ALTHOUGH THERE WAS A VERY
CLOSE CASE INVOLVING MARTHA
STEWART, A QUESTION OF FACT AS
WHO WAS TELLING THE TRUTH AND
WHO WASN'T.
IN THIS CASE THERE IS NO CASE OF
COLLUS
COLLUSION.
THAT'S NOT THE ONLY THING.
SECOND, THERE IS NONE OF THE
THINGS THAT YOU USUALLY HAVE
WITH AN OBSTRUCTION CASE.
LET'S TAKE THE FLYNN SITUATION
WHICH HE SAYS DIDN'T TAKE PLACE.
IF YOU TAKE HIS TESTIMONY HE
SAYS THE PRESIDENT SAID TO ME GO
EASY ON FLYNN.
THAT'S OBSTRUCTION.
I NEVER HEARD OF OBSTRUCTION
CASE.
I THINK IT BEGAN WITH PLEAS.
YOU NEVER START WITH PLEAS.
IT STARTS WITH TAKE YOUR MONEY
AWAY.
SOME THREAT INVOLVED IN IT.
SOME KIND OF COERCION.
FINALLY IT COULDN'T BE
OBSTRUCTION BECAUSE ASSUMING HE
IS TELLING THE TRUTH, SO WHAT
HAPPENED THERE MAY YOU FIGURED
OUT HE WAS OBSTRUCTED IN
FEBRUARY.
I'M GOING TO REPORT IT TO THE
FBI?
I THINK WE WILL KILL THAT
OBSTRUCTION THEORY.
>> WERE YOU SURPRISED?
>> I DESCRIBE IT AS A VERY VERY
OFFICIAL LEGAL TERM.
I DESCRIBE IT AS A LEGAL THEORY
OF OBSTRUCTION.
>> WERE YOU SURPRISED MUELLER
AND HIS TEAM DIDN'T SUBPOENA THE
PRESIDENT TO SEEK AN ORAL B
INTERVIEW?
>> YOU WERE BRACING FOR THAT
RIGHT?
>> WE COULD HAVE.■v I TOLD YOU,
OBSTRUCTION PART AFTER HE WAS
PRESIDENT I THINK WE HAD THE
BETTER ARGUMENT.
I THINK WE WOULD HAVE WON THAT
BATTLE PARTICULARLY BECAUSE WE
HAD SO MUCH INFORMATION.
WHAT YOU TO SHOW FLORD GET ■A
PRESIDENT'S TESTIMONY HE TRIED
TO RESIST THE SUBPOENA.
HE LOST.
THE COURT SAID YOU HAVE TO SHOW
IF YOU WANT TO SUBPOENA A
PRESIDENT THAT YOU CAN'T GET
THIS INFORMATION ANY OTHER WAY.
WE WERE PRETTY CONFIDENT
WHATEVSTIONSY WANTED ■@■@■@HEY
INFORMATION WHICH IS ALSO WHY
THEY SUSPECTED THEY WERE TRYING
TO TRAP HIM IN THE PERJURY.
WE DIDN'T NEED HIS EXPLANATIONS.
>> WHY DID HE FIRE COMEY?
>> HE GAVE ALL OF THE REASONS.
HE IS GOING TO REPEAT IT.
>> LET ME MENTION RUSSIA?
>>NO QUESTION RUSSIA HAD
SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT.
THERE WERE EIGHT OTHER REASONS
CHLS THAT ALL HE NEEDS.
HE HAD VERY VERY GOOD REASONS TO
FIRE HIM.
HILLARY WOULD HAVE FIRED THE GUY
I THINK.
>> WELL, HILLARY WOULD HAVE
FIRED HIM FOR OTHER REASONS.
>> COCOMEY DID NOT COVER
HIMSELF.
>> I HIRED JIM COMEY.
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T FLOW WHAT HAPPENED TO
HIM.
HE DID NOT COVER HIMSELF WITH
GLORY MANY THIS PARTICULAR CASE.
WHAT HE DID TO HILLARY CLINTON
IS WRONG.
YOU DON'T SAY I'M NOT GOING TO
INDICT AND THEN SAY ALL OF THE
BAD THINGS ABOUT SOMEBODY AND
YOU DON'T SAY I'M NOT GOING TO
INDICT BUT SAY I CAN'T
EXONERATE.
>> WAS THERE --
>> THAT'S A CLHEAP SHOT.
>> WAS THERE EVER A THOUGHT THAT
MUELLER WAS GOING TO ASK HIM TO
TESTIFY?
>> NO.
THERE WAS NEVER -- THAT NEVER
CAME UP.
SO WE NEVER FACED THE SITUATION.
WHAT DID HAPPEN PERSISTENTLY,
AND YOU HEARD SOME OF THESE,
THERE WERE RUMORS AND THEN WE
CHECK AND YOU GET ONE ABOUT
THREE OR FOUR WEEKS.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT THEY WERE TO
GET THE PRESIDENT ANGRY.
I CAN TELL YOU THE PRESIDENT
HANDLED THE STUFF AGAINST HIM
REALLY WELL.
THE PRESIDENT WOULD GET UPSET
WHEN IT INVOLVED HIS FAMILY OR
SOME OF THE PEOPLE THAT WORKED
FOR HIM OR SOME OF THE KIDS LIKE
SOME OF THESE PEOPLE YOU SEE ON
TELEVISION HAD TO SPEND AN
ENORMOUS AMOUNT OF MONEY.
>> AND IN THAT TRUMP TOWER
MEETING IN JUNE OF 2016 WHEN
THEY MET WITH THIS RUSSIAN THAT
SUPPOSEDLY.
HE SAID GREAT.
WE'LL TAKE IT.
>> JARED WAS IN ABOUT HALF OF
THE MEETING.
>> WERE YOU SURPRISED HAY DIDN'T
CALL ON THEM TO AT LEAST ANSWER
QUESTIONS?
>> I'M NOT SURPRISED BECAUSE I
THINK FROM THE PEOPLE ON THE
OTHER SIDE OF THAT MEETING I
DON'T THINK THEY EVER DISCUSSED
HILLARY CLINTON.
SO IT GOT SET UP THAT WAY BUT IT
REALLY WAS A PRETEXT TO TALK
ABOUT ADOPTIONS AND ADOPTIONS
FROM RUSSIA AND SO EVERYBODY
KIND OF WALKED OUT ON■P■  IT.
>> YOUR THOUGHTS ON GRAHAM
SAYING IT WAS HIS IDEA TO HAND
OVER THE DOSSIER TO THE FBI.
YOU HE SAY IT A LITTLE
WHILE AGO.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN REALLY
RAILING AGAINST THE LATE SENATOR
JOHN McCAIN BLAMING HIM FOR THIS
WHOLE THING.
GRAHAM SAYS I SUGGESTED TO H
HIMTH
HIM THERE'S A LOT OF DIRT IN
THERE.
>> I HAVEN'T READ ALL OF IT.
I READ A LOT OF WHAT'S IN THERE.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE SAW IT.
HE MAY HAVE BEEN DESCRIBED TO
HIM.
I THINK HE HAS A PROFESSIONAL
LAWYER WOULD REALIZE IT'S A
PIECE OF GARBAGE.
IT'S A SILLY DOCUMENT.
IT'S NOT A WELL WRITTEN
INTELLIGENCE DOCUMENT.
IT IS OBVIOUSLY -- IT LOOKS LIKE
A BIG LONG NATIONAL INQUIRER
ARTICLE.
IT DOESN'T SEEM TO COME FROM AN
INTEL
INTELLIGENCE PROFESSIONAL.
THE RUSSIANS MADE HIM AN AGENT
TEN YEARS AGO AND DECIDED FIVE
YEARS AGO HE WOULD BE PRESIDENT.
IF THEY COULD FIGUR OUT HE
WOULD BE PRESIDENT THEY WILL BE
IN A LOT OF TROUBLE.
THEY ARE A LOT SMARTER THAN THEY
THINK THEY ARE.
>> AND OTHER --
>> THERE IS ALSO ANOTHER THING
THEY DID WITH THAT THAT'S REALLY
THERE'S A SPECIFIC ALLEGATION IN
THERE THAT MICHAEL COHEN WENT TO
GET INFORMATION FOR THE
RUSSIANS.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL YOU TO DO IS THE DATE.
CALL THE STATE DEPARTMENT AND
FIND OUT WHAT DOES THIS PASSPORT
SAY?
THEY ARE DOING THIS
EXTRAORDINARY ACT.
A MAN TURNS OUT TO BE INNOCENT.
THEY DON'T EVEN BOTHER TO CHECK
THE ONE THING.
>> YOU KNOW TO SOUTHERN DISTRICT
OF NEW YORK.
YOU ONCE WERE THE U.S. ATTORNEY,
THEY ARE PRETTY AGGRESS IFR.
HOW WORRIED ARE YOU THAT THE
MUELLER INFORMATION 22 MONTHS IS
OVER WITH NOW BUT THEIR
INVESTIGATION FROM SOME FROM
SOME PERSPECTIVE IS ONLY JUST
BEGINNING.
>> IT HAS BEEN GOING ON BEFORE
THE SUMMER.
>> I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT IT AT
ALL.
THERE'S NO VIOLATION OF THE LAW.
WHEN YOU MAKE PAYMENTS TO SETTLE
PERSONAL CLAIM AND FEEVEN IF IT
HELPS IT CAN'T POSSIBLY BE A
CAMPAIGN CONTRIBUTION.
IT IS A VERY FAULTY LEGAL
THEORY.
>> THEY SITED IT AS A CAMPAIGN
CONTRIBUTION, THE MONEY THAT WAS
GIVEN.
>> LET THEM TRY TO INCITE
SOMEBODY.
THE COURT WILL THROW IT OUT.
>> HE PLEADED GUILTY.
IF IT CAN BE CONSIDERED A
CAMPAIGN CONTRIBUTION THECHB I
CAN RUN FOR OFFICE NOW.
I CAN SETTLE EVERY CASE AGAINST
ME AND USE MY DONORS MONEY TO DO
IT AND THEY WOULD PUT ME IN
JAIL.
THAT'S THE THEORY THEY HAVE AND
IT WILL FALL DOWN.
YOU NOTICED IN THAT DOCUMENT, IN
THAT CHARGE AGAINST MICHAEL
COHEN AND THE JUDGE ACCEPTED IT
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES IS IDENTIFIED AS
INDIVIDUAL NUMBER ONE.
>> WHETHER IT IS OR ISN'T IT'S
NOT A CRIME.
IF IT'S A CRIME THEN WE HAVE 30
PLUS MEMBERS OF CONGRESS WHO
OVER THE LAST SEVER YEARS HAVE
HAD CLAI CLAIMS OF SEXUAL HARAS.
>> DID THE PRESIDENT DO THAT?
>> WHAT?
>> WORK TO PAY OFF --
>> I'M NOT SAYING HE DID.
I'M TELLING YOU IF THEY TRY TO
ALLEGE THAT AS A CRIME IT IS IN
THE A CRIME.
HE WOULD HAVE A WEIRD SUCH WAYS
PEOPLE WOULD RUN TO CLEAN OUT
ALL OF THE CLIMBS AGAINST HIM
AND USE DONORS MONEY TO DO THAT.
IT WOULD BE AN ABACCIDENT
OCCURRED ABSURD APPLICATION.
>> AND YOU KNOW THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL, YOUR HOME STATEOVER NEW
YORK, THE STATE ATTORNEY
GENERAL, INVESTIGATING AND
SHE IS INVESTIGATING.
>> SHE RAN ON THE PLATFORM THAT
I'M GOING TO INVESTIGATE DONALD
TRUMP AND I'M GOING TO GET HIM
FOR SOMETHING.
VERY CREDIBLE.
>> SO YOU'RE NOT WORRIED
ABOUT --
>> SHE IS LOOKING AT THE
FOUNDATION.
HE PAID OUT 19 MILLION AND HE
RAISED ONLY 18 MILLION.
HE DONATED ABOUT 18 MILLION OF
HIS OWN MINUTE.
THERE'S NOT A SINGLE CLAIM THAT
NOBODY WAS PAID.
NO BIG SALARIES.
NO TRIPS PAID FOR.
NO PERKS, NOT $150 MILLION
CONTRIBUTION FROM RUSSIA LIKEE .
I DON'T THINK THERE'S A PROBLEM.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT
INVESTIGATING THE TRUMP
ORGANIZATION?
>> NO BECAUSE I THINK THE TRUMP
ORGANIZATION IS CLEAN.
IT'S A CLEAN ORGANIZATION.
SHEER WHAT I REALLY WORRY ABOUT
AS A CITIZEN.
THIS IS LIKE SAYING I'M GOING TO
GO BACK IN THIS MAN'S LIFER I'M
GOING TO GO BACK AND FIND
SOMETHING HE DID WRONG.
SO I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG IS THAT
GOING GO■á ON?
>> ARE YOU GOING TO STICK AROUND
AND CONTINUE THIS?
WHAT'S THE NEXT CLAP TER.
>> I DO A LOT OF OTHER THINGS.
I RUN A SECURITY BUSINESS AND WE
DO SECURITY CONSULTING.
>> I HEARD ON STRATEGISTS THAT
SAY HE DOESN'T THINK IT IS WISE
TO PURSUE IMPEACHMENTS.
>> JIM IS IN THE HOUSE --
>> SAY THAT --
>> HE SAID WE HAVE TO MOVE ON
THIS CHAPTER IS OVER WITH.
>> SHE HAD THE RIGHT STANDARD
POLITICALLY WHICH IS YOU HAVE TO
HAVE BIPARTISAN SUPPORT.
IF YOU DON'T IT WILL LOOK LIKE A
COMPLETELY POLITICAL WITCH HUNT.
I DON'T THINK YOU'LL GET
BIPARTISAN SUPPORT BASED ON
THIS.
I HAVE A PRETTY GOOD IDEA FOR
THE REST OF WHAT THEY HAVE.
>> LOOKING FORWARD TO GETTING A
FULL REPORT.
>> IF ANYTHING IS ELD BACK I
KNOW SOMEONE WILL SAY OH, MY
GOD.
>> I WOULD LIKE THE WHOLE TLING
TO BE OUT.
>> I'M SURE THE PRESIDENT IS
GRATEFUL FOR YOU.
>> I'M GRATEFUL THAT HOWEVER
THEY GOT THERE WRONG OR NOT
WRONG I'M GRATEFUL THAT AN
INNOCENT MAN WAS, YOU KNOW,
VINDICATED.
>> AND YOU'RE ALWAYS WELCOME TO
COME BACK INTO OUR SITUATION
ROOM.
HAVE YOU BEEN TO THE WHITE HOUSE
SITUATION ROOM?
>> YEAH.
>> I WAS IN RE BEGAN
ADMINISTRATION.
I GO WAY BACK ALMOST AS OLD AS
YOU.
>>■R MAYBE.
>> THANKS SO MUCH FOR COMING
OUT.
APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WE'LL HAVE A LOT MORE COMING
UP RIGHT AFTER THIS.
■■,
If you have postmenopausal
osteoporosis
and a high risk for fracture
now might not be the best time
to ask yourself
are my bones strong?
Life is full of make-or-break
moments.
That's why it's so importantçT
and protect bones from fracture
with 1 shot every 6 months.
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take
XGEVA®.
Serious allergic reactions,
like low blood pressure; trouble
breathing;
throat tightness; face, lip, or
tongue swelling;
rash; itching; or hives have
happened.
Tell your doctor about denta■■■
as severe jaw bone problems may
happen
or new or unusual pain in your
hip groin, or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone fractures
urred.
Speak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects,
like low blood calcium, serious
infections,
which could need
hospitalization, skin problems,
and severe bone, joint, or
muscle pain.
Are you ready?
Ask your doctor how Prolia® can
help strengthen your bones.
>>> JUSTICE DEPARTMENT SAID IT
WILL TAKE WEEKS FOR BILL BARR TO
MAKE A VERSION OF THE MUELLER
REPORT AVAILABLE.
I JUST SPOKE AT LENG WITH RUDY
GIULIANI.
WE HAVE A LOT TO DISCUSS.
SUSAN, LET ME GET YOUR THOUGHTS
ON WHAT WE JUST HEARD FROM THE
MAYOR.
>> IT IS DIFFICULT SO PARSE IT
ALL OUT.
AGAIN, THE BAR SUMMARY IS NOT
THE MUELLER REPORT.
APPARENTLY THE WHITE HOUSE HAS
NOT REVIEWED THE MUELLER REPORT
FOR THEMSELVES SO THEY ARE
MAKING -- OPERATING WITH SAME
INFORMATION WE ARE.
IN IT DOES NOT EXONERATE THE
PRESIDENT OR ANSWER SERIOUS
QUESTIONS ABOUT HIS CAMPAIGN'S
CONDUCT.
IT IS INTERESTING THAT JEWGIULI
ADMITTED HAD A RUSSIAN
INDIVIDUAL REACHED OUT THAT HE
WOULD HAVE BEEN INCLINED TO
CONTACT THE FBI.
I THINK IT GOES TO ONE OF THE
CORE QUESTIONS HERE WHICH IS
ROBERT MUELLER HAS NOW ANSWERED
THE QUESTION ABOUT WHETHER OR
NOT ANY CRIMINAL CONDUCT
OCCURRED.
I DOESN'T MEAN THAT UNACCEPTABLE
NOW WE'LL HAVE TO DECIDE IF WHAT
THE PRESIDENT DID WAS ACCEPTABLE
OR NOT.
ZB HE SAID HE WANTS EVERYTHING
RELEASED.
HE SAID IMPLIED YOU
RELEASE GRAND JURY TESTIMONY IF
YOU GET A JUDGE TO SAY OKAY.
WHAT WAS
HIS DESCRIPTION OF THE WRITTEN
QUESTIONS AND HOW THERE WERE
MULTIPLE PAGES, SEVEN OR EIGHT
OR WHATEVER IT WAS WITH SUB
TEXT.
WHEN YOU ASKED HIM WHY DIDN'T
YOU HAVE THE PRESIDENT TESTIFY
IF HE'S TELLING THE TRUTH, HE
SAID IT WOULD BE MALPRACTICE.
AND THAT IS OUR UNDERSTANDING OF
WHAT THE LAWYERS■& SAYING.
WHICH THEY WOULD LAY THEMSELVES
DOWN IN FRONT OF A BUS BEFORE
THEY'D LET DONALD TRUMP TESTIFY.
BUT I MUST SAY THIS IS SORT OF
THE FOR ME IN HEARING RUDY
GIULIANI, IT'S THE CALMEST I
HAVE EVER HEARD HIM ABOUT THIS
ENTIRE CASE BECAUSE THE RELIEF
IS PALPABLE FOR HIM.
I DO BELIEVE THE PRESIDENT IS
MISCHARACTERIZED THE
EXONERATION, OR SO-CALLED
EXONERATION OR ON OBSTRUCTION,
WHICH THERE WAS NONE, BUT YOU
CAN SEE THAT THE RELIEF IS
THERE.
AND THAT HE SAYS YET AGAIN, PUT
EVERYTHING OUT THERE.
IF HE'S SAYING PUT EVERYTHING
OUT THERE AND THE CONGRESS IS
SAYING PUT EVERYTHING OUT THERE
AND THE PRESIDENT IS SAYING PUT
VRG OUT THERE, WHY NOT?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I THINK THE RELIEF COULD BE
SHORT LIVED.
THE MUELLER REPORT, AS WE
UNDERSTAND IT, TO THE DEGREE
THAT IF FOUND THERE WAS NO
INSTITUTIONAL LEVEL CONSPIRACY
BETWEEN THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND
THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT, THE
PRESIDENT IS CLEAR.
BUT AS SUSAN POINTED OUT, WHAT
WE DON'T KNOW IS THE EXTENT TO
WHICH INDIVIDUALS ON THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGNEN ENGAGED IN ACTIVITIES
WITH RUSSIAN OFFICIALS THAT MAY
NOT HAVE RISEN TO THE LEVEL OF
CRIMINALITY, BUT STILL
COMPLETELY INAPPROPRIATE.
SO THAT'S A QUESTION THAT MUST
BE ANSWERED.
WE HAVE AN ISSUE OF OBSTRUCTION
OF JUSTICE.
WE DON'T KNOW THAT THE PRESIDENT
NEVER OBSTRUCTED JUSTICE IS
BASED ON PREEXISTING NOTION■  TT
A PRESIDENT CAN'T BE GUILTY OR
IF IT WAS BASED ON A WELCOME OF
EVIDENCE AND ONLY THE REPORT
WILL HELP US UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> THE MAYOR RUDY GIULIANI SAID
HE WOULD BE FINE RELEASING THE
WRITTEN Q&A THE PRESIDENT
ENGAGED IN WITH ROBERT MUELLER.
HE WOULDN'T HAVE IS A PROBLEM.
>> HE SAID HE WANTS IT ALL OUT
THERE.
WHAT'S INTERESTING IS HIS
CHARACTER RAIGS.
THE PRESIDENT WAS ASKED IF HE
THOUGHT HE WAS AN HONORABLE MAN
AND HE SAID YES.
RUDY GIULIANI SAID HE DISAGREED
WITH THE PRESIDENT AND SAID HE
WASN'T HONORABLE AT LEAST IN HOW
HE HANDLED THIS INVESTIGATION.
AND ALSO I THOUGHT IT WAS
STRIKING THAT HE SAID THAT
ROBERT MUELLER MAY HAVE BEEN
CONFUSED WHEN TRY ING TO DECIDE
ON WHETHER THE PRESIDENT
OBSTRUCTED JUSTICE AND THAT'S
WHY IN HIS WORDS HE PUNTED.
AND THEN HE REALLY DID GO AFTER
PROSECUTION AS WELL.
SOME OF THE OTHER PROSECUTORS
THERE, CALLING HIM MUELLER'S
HENCHMAN AND THEN THE OTHER
THING THAT STRUCK ME WAS WHEN
YOU ASKED ABOUT A PARDON FOR
MANAFORT AND HE MAY HAVE
COMMITTED A CRIME BUT DOESN'T DO
SOMETHING SO EGREGIOUS TO BE
TREATED THE WAY HE WAS.
>> IT'S INTERESTING.
THE FULL ISSUE OF PARDONS, HE
SAID MANAFORT WAS TREATED
UNFAIRLY BY THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
AND MICHAEL FLYNN, THE FORMER
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER WAS
BADLY TREATED AS WELL.
>> BUT HE SAID■ WE HAVEN'T
DISCUSSED PARDONS.
M
IT'S THE COUNSEL'S JOB IN THE
WHITE HOUSE.
HE'S RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
BUT WHAT WAS INTERESTING TO ME
IS IT'S CLEAR THAT WHAT STICKS
IN THE PRESIDENT'S CRAW AND RUDY
GIULIANI IS IS THE LINE THAT
SAYS THAT WE CAN'T CONCLUDE THE
PRESIDENT COMMITTED A CRIME, BUT
IT DOES NOT EXONERATE HIM.
IT'S CLEAR THAT RUDY GIULIANI
BELIEVES THE SECOND PART OF THAT
WAS SOMETHING THAT A SPECIAL
COUNSEL SHOULD NOT SAY BECAUSE
IF YOU CAN'T PROVE IT, YOU
SHOULDN'T SAY HE'S NOT
EXONERATED.
>> THE MAYOR SAID THAT WHEN THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL ROBERT MUELLER
COULDN A FINAL DECISION
ON THE WHOLE ISSUE OF
OBSTRUCTION HE WAS HANDING IT
OVER TO THE ATTORNEY GENERAL TO
MAKE THAT DECISION.
>> SO ONCE AGAIN, WE DON'T KNOW
THAT'S WHAT ROBERT MUELLER
INTENDED AT ALL UNTIL WE SEE
THAT UNDERLYING REPORT.
ROBERT MUELLER SAID, THIS DOES
NOT EXONERATE HIM.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE HE'S PRESENT
ING THE LEGAL ARGUMENTS ON BOTH
SIDES.
AND HE'S GOING TO LEAVE THAT FOR
CONGRESS TO DECIDE.
I THINK WHEN WE'RE SEEING IS THE
WHITE HOUSE STRATEGY THAT
BETWEEN THE BARR SUMMARY AND
MUELLER REPORT TO CAPITALIZE ON
THE CHAOS AND CONFUSION IS AND
THROW AS MUCH SAND AS POSSIBLE
IN HOPING A TO GET A NARRATIVE
THAT WILL STICK.
>> IT'S POSSIBLE ALSO THAT THERE
WAS SOME DISAGREEMENT AMONG THE
LAWYERS WORKING FOR MUELLER.
AND THAT THEY HAD A DIFFICULT
TIME CLEARLY, REACHING SOME KIND
OF DECISION.
HE DID PUNT IT.
NOW WHETHER HE EXPECTED BARR TO
MAKE THAT DECISION OR NOT
REMAINS TO BE SEEN.
>> WE'LL HAVE A LOT MORE ON THIS
COMING UP.
HAVE TO TAKE ANOTHER QUICK
BREAK.
OTHER IMPORTANT NEWS WE'RE ALSO
FOLLOWING IN A STUNNING TWIST, A
PROSECUTOR DROPS 16 FELONY
COUNTS AGAINST JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
I'LL TALK TO CHICAGO'S MAYOR
RAHM EMANUEL, HE'S STANDING BY
LIVE AND CALLING IT AWHITEWASH.
I'LL ALSO DISCUSS THEHING ■■■ WC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE KAMALA
HARRIS.
SHE'S HERE LIVE IN THE SITUATION
ROOM.
Hi.
Maria Ramirez!
Mom!
Maria!
Maria Ramirez...
McDonald's is committing
150 million dollars
in tuition assisnce,
education, and caree
advising programs...
Mom and Dad: Maria Ramirez!!!
to help mo employees
achieve their dreams.
Now, eyeliner goes NYC-proof.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil
Mom and Dad: Maria Ramirez!!!
from Maybelline New York.
Smudge resistant.
Sweat resistant.
Waterproof.
Up to 36-hour wear
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil.
Only from Maybelline New York.
They're America's
biopharmaceutical researchers.
Pursuing life-changing cures
in a country that fosters
innovation
Here, they find breakthroughs...
Like a way to fight cancer
by arming a patient's own
T-cells...
Because it's not just about
the next breakthrough...
It's all the ones after that.
(VO)
We're Carvana,
the company who invented
car vending machines
and buying a car
100% online.
Now we've created a brand new
way for you to sell your car.
Whether it's a few years old
or dinosaur old,
we want to buy your car.
So go to Carvana
and enter your license plate,
answer a few questions,
and our techno-wizardry
calculates your car's value
and gives you a real offer
in seconds.
When you're ready,
we'll come to you,
pay you on the spot,
and pick up your car. Thñ
So ditch the old way
of selling your car
and say hello
to the new way...
at Carvana.
You're turning onto the
street
when you barely
clip a passing car.
Minor accident
—no big deal, right?
Wrong. Your insurance
company is gonna raise
your rate after the other
car got a scratch so small
you coulda fixed
it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that
pen and use it to sign up
with a different
insurance company.
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because of
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪