>>> GOOD MORNING.
IT IS 8:00 A.M. AT PINTEREST
HEADQUARTERS IN SAN FRANCISCO,
8:00 A.M. AT ZOOM HEADQUARTERS
IN SAN JOSE.
IT'S 11:00 A.M. ON WALL STREET
AND "SQUAWK ALLEY" IS LIVE.
♪
>>> GOOD THURSDAYS MORNING.
WELCOME TO "SQUAWK ALLEY."
I'M CARL QUINTANILLA WITH MORGAN
BRENNAN, DAVID FABER AT THE
NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE.
YOU GOT PINTEREST SET TO DEBUT
SHORTLY.
JON FORTT LIVE AT THE NASDAQ AS
WE AWAIT ZOOM'S OPENING TRADE
THERE, AWFULLY BIG SHOW AHEAD
THIS HOUR.
WE'LL TALK TO PINTEREST BEN
SILVERMAN IMMEDIATELY AFTER THAT
STOCK OPENS AND ZOOM'S ERIC YUAN
WILL BE WITH US LIVE FROM THE
NASDAQ AFTER THAT DEBUT.
WE'LL START WITH ZOOM AND JON
WITH THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: AS YOU CAN SEE WE
GOT ABOUT TWO AND A HALF MILLION
SHARES, INDICATIVE PRICE IS 60
BUCKS A SHARE, PRETTY REMARKABLE
CONSIDERING THEY'RE PRICED AT 36
AND WE JUST HEARD LESS THAN TEN
MINUTES AGO HERE THAT MORGAN
STANLEY IS IN NO RUSH.
I'M TOLD TRYING TO BE DILIGENT
PUTTING THIS TOGETHER.
MORGAN STANLEY ALSO INVOLVED
WITH LYFT ABOUT THREE WEEKS AGO
AND SO WE WAIT HERE, THE CROWD
FROM ZOOM IS HERE --
>> JON, WE'LL TRY TO WORK ON
YOUR MIC IN A MOMENT.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY IT'S LOUD HERE
AND LOUD THERE.
IN THE MEANTIME WE'LL TURN TO
PINTEREST.
>> WE ARE GOING TO TURN TO
AS YOU CAN SEE RIGHT BEHIND US,
INDICATED 23 TO 25, 23 TO 75 SO
THAT RANGE DOES SEEM TO BE
NARROWING, WHAT WE HEARD FROM
BOB PISANI JUST IN THE LAST
FINAL MOMENTS OF THE LAST HOUR
IS THAT THIS IS POISED TO OPEN
IN THE COMING MINUTES.
WE'LL GO BACK OVER THERE AND GET
AN UPDATE FROM BOB, HEY.
>> Reporter: I THINK THE
IMPORTANT THING HERE IS WE ARE
WAITING FOR IT TO OPEN AND IT
HAS BEEN AROUND THE 23 PRICE, 23
TO 23.50 FOR MORE THAN 45
MINUTES NOW.
THAT'S A GOOD INDICATION THAT
MOST OF THE TIME IT'LL SETTLE
SOME WHERE AROUND THERE.
IT DOESN'T ALWAYS HAPPEN.
WITH PAGERDUTY, 29 PRICE, ALL OF
A SUDDEN A WAVE OF ORDERS CAME
IN BECAUSE PEOPLE SAID I'LL SELL
IT AT THAT PRICE, I'LL SELL A
LOT OF IT AND THE PRICE HAD TO
DROP.
THE DEMAND SEEMS TO BE FAIRLY
STEADY.
LET'S SEE IF I CAN GET AN
UPDATE.
WE HEARD ABOUT THE POTENTIAL FOR
15 MINUTES A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
GLENN KURELL, YOU'VE BEEN DOING
THIS A LONG TIME, WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN?
>> WE'RE STILL IN A GOOD RANGE.
NOW WE'RE JUST WAITING ON A
COUPLE MORE PLAYERS TO GET IN
THE GAME OF THE WE'RE HAPPY WITH
THE WAY THINGS GOOD LOOK RIGHT
NOW.
THE BOOK IS LINING UP GREAT.
WE'RE FULLY TRANSPARENT AS TO
WHERE WE LOOK.
NOW WE'RE JUST WAITING ON ONE OR
TWO PLAYERS TO MAKE A COUPLE
ADJUSTMENTS AND WE'RE GOOD TO
GO.
>> Reporter: WHAT ARE THEY
TRYING TO DECIDE TO DO
ARE THEY TRYING TO BID FOR MORE
OR OFFER MORE?
>> THEY DON'T WANT TO MISS THE
PRINT AT THE SAME TIME.
IF SOMEONE IS BIDDING 23.25,
MAYBE THEY WANT TO COME UP TO
23.50.
THOSE ARE THE THINGS WE'RE
LOOKING AT RIGHT NOW.
>> Reporter: THE FACT THAT WE'VE
BEEN AT 23 FOR THE LAST 45
MINUTES OR SO, IS THIS A PRETTY
GOOD BET THAT'S WHERE WE'RE
GOING TO OPEN.
>> LIKE I SAID, WE HAVE THE
VOLUME THERE.
EVERYTHING'S LINED UP ON OUR
END.
OUR TECHNOLOGY IS READY TO GO.
WE'RE JUST WAITING.
>> Reporter: WHAT DO YOU LIKE TO
SEE IN AN OPEN IN TERMS OF
VOLUME.
IS THERE A PERCENTAGE GENERALLY
THAT YOU LIKE TO SEE, 10% OF THE
FLOAT OF THE AMOUNT OF SHARES
THAT ARE BEING SOLD?
WHAT'S A GOOD NUMBER
>> IT'S NOT A RULE OF THUMB, WE
LIKE TO GET 10%.
I THINK WE'LL BE CLOSER TO 9 TO
10 MILLION SHARES WHICH IS
REALLY HEALTHY.
WE'LL BE READY TO GO.
>> Reporter: GLENN, THANKS VERY
MUCH.
I ASKED ABOUT THE PERCENTAGE
BECAUSE THE VOLUME IS A VERY
GOOD INDICATION OF OVERALL
INVESTOR INTEREST.
IF THEY FLOAT 9 MILLION OR 10
MILLION THAT'S MORE THAN 10% OF
THE AMOUNT OF SHARES SOLD.
IF YOU CLOSE AT THE END OF THE
DAY WITH CLOSE TO 100%, THAT'S
GENERALLY AN INDICATION OF A
VERY SUCCESSFUL IPO THAT THERE'S
ACTIVE TRADING THAT'S INVOLVED.
THESE ARE JUST ROUGH RULES OF
THUMB.
PEOPLE ARE USING, 23 TO 23.50,
HOLD ON ONE MINUTE.
IT'S LOOKING CLOSER TO AROUND 23
TO 23.50 LEVEL.
GETTING CLOSE.
TEN TO 15 MINUTES LOOKS LIKE.
WE'LL BE HERE.
BACK TO YOU.
>> WE'RE GOING TO WATCH AND
WATCH THE MUELLER REPORT WHICH
IS NOW ON THE JUSTICE WEBSITE.
JON FORTT'S BACK AT THE NASDAQ
WATCHING ZOOM.
JON, HELLO ONCE AGAIN.
>> Reporter: LET'S TRY THIS
AGAIN.
62, IT'S GONE UP TWO BUCKS SINCE
THE LAST TIME YOU SAW ME,
2.5 MILLION SHARES PAIRED.
THIS WOULD BE MORE THAN 70%
ABOVE THE INITIAL PRICING.
SO THAT IS SIGNIFICANT.
ALSO WE HEARD ABOUT TEN MINUTES
AGO MORGAN STANLEY'S IN NO RUSH
TO GET THIS OUT, TRYING TO BE
DILIGENT, OF COURSE.
YOU'LL RECALL MORGAN STANLEY WAS
INVOLVED IN LYFT ABOUT THREE
WEEKS AGO AND THE FOLKS AT ZOOM
THROUGHOUT HERE JUST EAGERLY
AWAITING THE OPENING OF THE
STOCK.
I WAS TALKING TO THE CEO JUST A
FEW MINUTES AGO, MAYBE ABOUT AN
HOUR AGO, TALKING ABOUT THE
CULTURE OF THE COMPANY, HOW
IMPORTANT IT IS TO KEEP THOSE
EMPLOYEES HAPPY AS THEY CONTINUE
ON THEIR JOURNEY OF GROWTH.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO TALKING
TO HIM MORE ONCE THIS STOCK
OPENS.
LET ME TOSS IT OVER TO BERTHA
COOMBS ACROSS THE ROOM.
>> Reporter: WHAT WE'VE HEARD SO
FAR IS WE'RE ABOUT 15 MINUTES
AWAY BUT IF YOU LISTEN TO JAY
HELLER HERE THE HEAD OF CAPITAL
MARKETS AT NASDAQ, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE IN THE RANGE OF 62 TO 63.
THEY WOULD LIKE TO PAIR OFF 3
MILLION SHARES OR SO.
THEY'RE TRYING TO COAX MORE
SELLERS TO SELL SO THE BUYING
INTERESTS WILL HAVE SOMETHING TO
PICK UP.
THIS COULD TAKE A WHILE.
HE SAID MAYBE ABOUT 15 MINUTES
OR SO, BUT WE HEARD THAT ABOUT A
HALF HOUR AGO, SO THEY ARE NOT
GOING TO RUSH THIS PROCESS AT
THE MOMENT, FOLKS HERE VERY
INTERESTED IN WATCHING THE
SITUATION AS YOU CAN SEE.
ZOOM, AGAIN, IS ONE OF THOSE
COMPANIES THAT IS PROFITABLE.
IT DOES VIDEO CONFERENCING BUT
IT ALSO WORKS AS A NUMBER OF
SILICON VALLEY COMPANIES WHICH
IS AMONG THE BIDDERS HERE AND
AMONG THE COMPANIES GETTING AN
ALLOCATION OF $100 MILLION AT
THAT $36 PER SHARE PRICE, CARL.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> JOINING US ON THE PHONE THIS
MORNING, COFOUNDER AND EARLY
FACEBOOK INVESTOR, OF COURSE,
AUTHOR OF "ZUCKED" WAKING UP TO
THE FACEBOOK CATASTROPHE.
THANKS FOR THE TIME.
>> ISN'T IT FUN TO HAVE A BLAND
MARKET.
>> I GOT TO ASK YOU, WHICH OF
THESE TWO BOILING POTS IS MORE
INTERESTING TO YOU
I WOULD IMAGINE IT'S PINTEREST
GIVEN YOUR INTEREST IN SOCIAL
BUT MAYBE NOT.
>> TO BE CLEAR, ZOOM IS THAT
MOST NEARBY FEAT WHICH IS A
PROFITABLE IPO COMING OUT OF THE
TECH SECTOR AND YOU CAN SEE THAT
THE APPETITE FOR THE URN
CERTAINTY OF PROFITS IS MAKING
PEOPLE PAY ANY PRICE NECESSARY
TO OWN A PIECE OF IT SO FROM A
STOCK MARKET POINT OF VIEW
THAT'S THE ONE I FIND
COMPELLING.
THAT SAID, I THINK PINTEREST'S
STRATEGY FOR GOING PUBLIC IS
BRILLIANT.
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS THE LAST
TIME I WAS ON, THE NOTION OF
PRICING WELL UNDER THE LAST
PRIVATE ROUND BROUGHT A LOT OF
PEOPLE INTO THE MARKET.
SO THEY'LL HAVE A VERY
SUCCESSFUL IPO AND IT WOULD
SURPRISE NO ONE IF THE THING
FINISHED THE DAY WELL ABOVE ITS
LAST PRIVATE ROUND HAVING LURED
PEOPLE IN WITH THE POSSIBILITY
OF A REAL BARGAIN.
>> ROGER, I REALIZE THAT
PINTEREST HAS BEEN DISTANCING
ITSELF FROM THIS LABEL OF SOCIAL
MEDIA COMPANY, ARE FIRST TO
CONSIDER IT SELF A VISUAL
PLATFORM.
IT SHOULD BE LUMPED IN WITH THAT
CATEGORY JUST FROM THE VALUATION
PERSPECTIVE, BUT HOW DO YOU SEE
IT
>> YOU KNOW THE LABEL ISN'T -- I
THINK -- THE LABEL OF SOCIAL
MEDIA USED TO BE A HUGE POSITIVE
NOW ALL OF A SUDDEN IT'S A
PROBLEM THAT PEOPLE ARE RUNNING
FROM IT.
WHAT'S GOING TO MATTER ON
PINTEREST IS HOW THE COMMUNITY
THAT USES IT USED THE PRODUCT
AND HOW -- AND HOW BAD ACTORS
USE THE PRODUCT.
THEY'VE BEEN ABLE TO MAINTAIN A
PLACE WHERE IN GENERAL THE
BEHAVIOR IS REALLY POSITIVE AND
SO IN MY MIND WE NEED A NEW
GENERATION OF SOCIAL PRODUCT
THAT ARE NOT OVERRUN BY TROLLS,
NOT OVERRUN BY BAD ACTORS AND IF
PINTEREST CAN PLAY A ROLE IN
THAT THEN THEY CAN GIVE SOCIAL
MEDIA A GOOD NAME AGAIN.
>> JON FORTT HERE AT THE NASDAQ
AWAITING THIS ZOOM IPO OPEN.
WE TALKED A BIT ABOUT VAL
EDUCATION IN THE PAST,
PROFITABILITY, RIGHT NOW ZOOM IF
IT OPENS AS IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S
GOING TO BE ABOVE 62 BUCKS A
SHARE, JUST REALLY A SKY HIGH
VALUATION, BUT IT'S PROFITABLE,
HOW DO YOU BALANCE THOSE TWO
THINGS YOU THINK
>> JON, I DON'T KNOW HOW THIS IS
GOING TO TURN OUT WITH THE FED
GOING TO A MUCH MORE
CONCILIATORY TONE.
JUST BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, WE'RE
LATE IN THE MARKET CYCLE,
VALUATIONS ARE ALREADY
INCREDIBLY HIGH, THERE'S A LOT
OF CASH STILL IN THE MARKET AND
NOW YOU HAVE THIS IPOs THAT WE
JUST SEE REALLY LOONEY BEHAVIOR
GOING ON IN THE BEST OF THOSE
DEALS AS PART OF A SPECULATIVE
BLOWOFF.
THAT WOULD HONESTLY BE A
FANTASTIC THING WHILE IT LASTS,
BUT, YOU KNOW, I HAVE NO IDEA IF
THAT'S WHAT'S GOING ON OR NOT
BUT LOOKED AT ZOOM, IT CERTAINLY
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GETTING, SHALL
WE SAY, UNRESTRAINED ENTHUSIASM.
>> ROGER, IT'S DAVID FABER.
THOSE THAT MUST HAVE LIVED
THROUGH THE DOTCOM BOOM, YOU
HAVE A TODAY LIKE TODAY TO THESE
IPOs, IT BRINGS IT TO MIND AS
SOMEBODY WHO ALSO LIVED THROUGH
THAT, GIVE ME SOME OF YOUR TAKE
IN TERMS OF THE SIMILARITIES AND
THE DISCREPANCIES BETWEEN THE
CURRENT PERIOD AND THAT ONE.
>> WE BOTH KNOW -- WHERE THEY
WERE SPENDING $2 TO GENERATE A
$1 OF REVENUE AND OBVIOUSLY HAVE
SITUATIONS LIKE THAT.
IF THE MARKET IS WILLING TO PAY
$100 MILLION VALUATION OR
$10 BILLION, GIVEN THE UNPROVEN
NATURE OF THAT BUSINESS MODEL,
THEN I THINK WE CAN COMFORTABLY
SAY -- THE BEHAVIOR OF THE DAY
IS CERTAINLY REMINISCENT OF '99
EXCEPT THERE WERE VERY FEW
THINGS IN '99 THAT HAD PROFIT.
YOU COULD MAKE THE CASE THAT --
PEOPLE CHASING PERFORMANCE --
>> ROGER, WE'VE BEEN TALKING A
LOT ABOUT THIS IDEA THAT IT'S
FAVORABLE MARKET CONDITIONS FOR
COMPANIES TO GO PUBLIC THAT YOU
HAVE LESS VOLATILITY THAN WE SAW
AT THE END OF LAST YEAR, STOCKS
AND MAJOR AVERAGES NEAR OR AT
HIGHS FOR THE YEAR OR ALL-TIME
HIGHS, I WONDER IF WE SHOULD BE
TALKING MORE ABOUT THE DOVISH
FED AND THE LID THAT'S PUT ON
INTEREST RATES ESPECIALLY WHEN
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT SOME OF
THESE HIGH GROWTH TECH UNICORNS
THAT ARE NOW COMING TO MARKET?
>> I'M WITH YOU COMPLETELY.
I THINK THE FED IS -- I THINK
THE FED SET UP THE CONDITION
FOR, YOU KNOW, A SPECULATIVE
BUBBLE HERE AND INVESTORS SHOULD
LOOK -- WHILE IT LASTS IT'S
GOING TO BE JUST REALLY, REALLY
FUN, BUT YOU WON'T BE THE LAST
ONE LOOKING FOR A CHAIR WHEN THE
MUSIC STOPS.
>> ROGER, THANK YOU.
>> NO GUARANTEE THAT'S WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN BUT IT SURE
FEELS THAT WAY.
THANK YOU.
>> ALWAYS GREAT TO GET YOUR
THOUGHTS AS WE DO AWAIT
PINTEREST'S OPENING TRADE HERE
JUST MOMENTS AWAY.
THE PRESIDENT OF THE NEW YORK
STOCK EXCHANGE JOINS US HERE AT
POST NINE.
STACEY, QUITE A BUSY DAY.
>> IT'S A GREAT DAY.
IT'S REALLY EXCITE TO GO WELCOME
PINTEREST TO THE NEW YORK STOCK
EXCHANGE.
A LOT OF INTEREST IN THIS DEAL
AND SO WE'RE WAITING FOR IT TO
OPEN BUT WE'RE EXCITED
IT'S A GREAT MORNING.
>> GOING BACK TO THE QUESTION I
JUST ASKED ROGER, HOW WOULD YOU
ASSESS THE MARKET SITUATION?
>> CERTAINLY INVESTORS ARE
CONTINUING TO EXPRESS INTERESTS
IN THESE DEALS, A LOT OF THEM
ARE PRICING ABOVE THE RANGE AND
OPENING EVEN STRONGER.
WE AREN'T SEEING INVESTORS PULL
BACK AT ALL.
THERE'S A LOT OF EXCITEMENT FOR
WHAT'S IN THE PIPELINE.
>> IN TERMS OF THE SO-CALLED
TECH UNICORNS THAT ARE COMING TO
MARKET RIGHT NOW AND REALLY IN
THE LAST COUPLE OF YEARS, THE
NASDAQ HAD ALWAYS SORT OF
HISTORICALLY BEEN SEEN AS THE
MORE TECH HEAVY AREA, BUT THE
STOCK EXCHANGE HAS BEEN
GATHERING OR WINNING MANY MORE
OF THESE HIGH PROFILE IPOs, HOW
HAVE YOU BEEN ABLE TO DO THAT
AND WHAT'S YOUR OUTLOOK?
>> ONE THING THAT'S IMPORTANT TO
RECOGNIZE IS TODAY'S COMPANY
LOOK VERY DIFFERENT THAN SOME OF
THE COMPANIES WE WELCOMED TO THE
MARKETS YEARS AGO.
THE NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE USED
TO REQUIRE COMPANIES TO BE
PROFITABLE BEFORE THEY COULD
LIST AND THAT'S NOT WHAT WE'RE
SEEING AS YOU KNOW WITH SOME OF
THE COMPANIES COMING OUT TO
MARKET.
WE MODERNIZED OUR LISTING RULES
TO REFLECT MORE WHAT WE'RE
SEEING IN THE PUBLIC COMPANIES
TODAY.
IF YOU LOOK BACK OVER THE PAST
FIVE YEARS, OVER 10% OF TECH
PROCEEDS HAVE BEEN RAISED ON THE
NYSE.
SO WE'RE EXCITED ABOUT THAT.
>> WHAT'S THE PINCH?
IN OTHER WORDS, YOU GO UP FOR AN
UBER AGAINST NASDAQ AND OTHERS,
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS ACTUALLY
WORKING IN YOUR FAVOR IN TERMS
OF YOUR ABILITY TO MARKET TO
THESE COMPANIES TO SAY COME
HERE
>> FIRST OF ALL, THIS IS THE
PITCH, WE PRICE DISCOVERY IS OUR
FORTE.
WE TAKE OUR TIME AND FIND THE
RIGHT PRICE.
WE'RE NOT JUST LOOKING FOR WHERE
THERE'S AN EQUILL LIB RUM.
WHEN A STOCK OPENS IT'S TRADE AT
A STABLE LEVEL.
THE MARKET MODEL IS NUMBER ONE
WHEN IT COMES TO WHAT
DIFFERENTIATES US AND WHAT WE
CAN OFFER COMPANIES AND THAT'S
NOT JUST ON IPO DAY.
WHEN THEIR IPO IS EXECUTED
FLAWLESSLY, SURE, THE MARKET
MODEL SHINES THERE BUT FOR THE
LIFE OF THE COMPANY WE TRADE
WITH LESS VOLATILITY WHICH SAVES
THEIR INVESTORS MON AND THEIR
OWN COMPANY MONEY.
BEYOND THAT, THE S&P 500 IS
LISTED ON THE NEW YORK STOCK
EXCHANGE AND THE BRAND
VISIBILITY THAT WE CAN GIVE THEM
TO SHARE ALONG WITH THE SUITE OF
SERVICES THAT WE PROVIDE.
SO THAT'S THE PITCH.
>> SO YOU OPENLY USE EXAMPLES
LIKE LYFT AS CAUTIONARY TALES?
>> WE TRY TO AVOID TALKING ABOUT
SPECIFIC DEALS.
WE TALK ABOUT WHAT WE CAN DO TO
DELIVER VALUE TO OUR LISTING
COMPANIES, HOW WE CAN ASSIST
THEM THROUGH THEIR PROCESS AND
WE TALK A LOT ABOUT WHAT WE DO,
HOW WE DO IT AND WHY WE DO IT.
>> HOW LONG DO YOU THINK IT
GOES, THE WAVE OF IPOs
>> IT'S HARD TO SAY.
>> BACK HALF OF THE YEAR, NEXT
YEAR
>> A LOT OF THE BIGGER COMPANIES
ARE COMING TO MARKET RIGHT NOW.
WHERE WE'D LIKE TO FOCUS
ATTENTION IS MAKING SURE SOME OF
THE SMALLER COMPANIES ARE ALSO
LOOKING TO COME TO THE PUBLIC
MARKET SOONER.
WE NEED TO RIGHT SIZE SOME OF
THE REGULATION THAT'S EXIST AND
WE NEED TO FOCUS ON MAKING SURE
THAT THEY'RE ENCOURAGED TO COME,
REMOVING BARRIERS THAT MIGHT
KEEP THEM PRIVATE FOR LONGER AND
IF WE WANT TO KEEP THAT PIPELINE
GOING.
>> BARRIERS LIKE -- ARE THEY A
REASON SOME OF THESE COMPANIES
HAVE BEEN PRIVATE FOR SO LONG?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THERE ARE A NUMBER OF DIFFERENT
THINGS.
SOME OF THE TOPICS THAT WE TALK
A LOT ABOUT LIKE DUAL CLASS
STRUCTURES, LIKE CERTAIN ESG
INITIATIVES OR GUIDELINES YOU
MIGHT WANT TO PUT ON PUBLIC
COMPANIES, THOSE ARE ALL THINGS
THAT GO INTO THE CALCULUS AS TO
WHETHER OR NOT THEY WANT TO STAY
PRIVATE OR PUBLIC.
WE WANT TO MAKE SURE WE'RE
ENCOURAGING THEM TO ACCESS THE
PUBLIC MARKET BECAUSE INVESTORS
GET TO SHARE ONCE THEY'RE PUBLIC
AND THE EVERYDAY INVESTOR
DOESN'T HAVE ACCESS TO PRIVATE
MARKETS THE WAY LARGE INVESTORS
DO.
>> TO THAT POINT, ONE OF THE
CONVERSATIONS WE'VE BEEN HAVING
AND CERTAINLY THIS RESTOKED
AFTER THE LYFT IPO A COUPLE
WEEKS AGO IS THE FACT THAT
RETAIL INVESTORS DON'T HAVE
ACCESS TO THE SAME AMOUNT OF
INFORMATION ABOUT A COMPANY
THAT'S COMING PUBLIC AS THE
INSTITUTIONAL INVESTORS.
DO YOU THINK THAT NEEDS TO
CHANGE
>> I THINK THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE
ASKING THAT QUESTION.
I THOUGHT IT WAS REALLY
INTERESTING TO SEE WHEN SPOTIFY
CAME TO THE MARKET, THAT WAS ONE
OF THE THINGS THEY WANTED TO
ADDRESS.
THEY MADE ALL THE INFORMATION
AVAILABLE TO ALL INVESTORS AT
THE SAME TIME, PUBLICLY
AVAILABLE ON THEIR WEBSITE AND
RETAIL INVESTORS HAVE THE SAME
ACCESS TO INSTITUTIONAL
INVESTORS.
I DON'T KNOW THAT WE'LL SEE A
NUMBER OF COMPANIES GOING DOWN
THAT PATH BUT THAT WAS ONE OF
THEIR GOALS AND IT WORKED FOR
THEM.
>> TO YOUR POINT, WE HAVE SEEN
COMPANIES STAY PRIVATE LONGER IN
PART BECAUSE THERE'S A MUCH
DEEPER PRIVATE MARKET THAN THERE
WAS 15, 20 YEARS AGO.
DO YOU REALLY THINK EVEN WITH
SOME REG CHANGES THAT THAT IS
GOING TO CHANGE?
THERE IS AN ARGUMENT THAT SAYS A
LOT OF THE GROWTH CURVE OCCURS
WHILE THESE ARE PRIVATE
COMPANIES AND THEREFORE YOUR
PUBLIC INVESTORS ARE NOT ABLE TO
PARTICIPATE IN IT.
>> THE GROWTH CURVE IS HAPPENING
EARLIER IN THE LIFE CYCLE.
THAT'S WHERE IT IS STEEPEST.
WE DO WANT TO SEE COMPANIES
COMING PUBLIC EARLIER.
I COULD LOOK AT BUILDING OUT A
PRIVATE MARKET PLATFORM AT THE
NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE BUT I
THINK IT'S THE WRONG ANSWER FOR
INVESTORS AND I THINK THAT
CONTRIBUTES TO A BIFURCATION OF
WEALTH THAT WE SEE HERE WHEN THE
MOST DYNAMIC FASTEST GROWING
COMPANIES ARE LEFT FOR LARGE
INVESTORS THAT HAVE ACCESS.
TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTION WHETHER
OR NOT IT MAKES A CHANGE IF WE
CHANGE SOME OF THOSE
REGULATIONS, IT'S PART OF THE
PROCESS AND I THINK THAT
CONVEYING THAT MESSAGE TO
COMPANIES THAT BY PROVIDING
OPPORTUNITIES FOR INVESTORS TO
SHARE IN THE SUCCESS, THEY'RE
ACTUALLY CONTRIBUTING TO WEALTH
FORMATION IN THIS NATION MORE
BROADLY IS PART OF THE EQUATION.
I THINK THAT WILL RESONATE WITH
SOME PEOPLE.
>> STACEY, THANKS.
>> THANKS.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> WE'RE GET TO GO THAT TIME.
>>> IT IS THE HOUR WHERE WE SAY
WE'RE CLOSE AND I THINK WE'RE ON
THAT FRONT WE'LL GO TO JON FORTT
AS WE CONTINUE TO WATCH ZOOM,
JON.
>> Reporter: I JUST GOT A THREE
MINUTE WARNING ON ZOOM AS YOU
CAN SEE THE PRICE NOW $63 A
SHARE.
THIS PRICED AT 36 LAST NIGHT.
THAT WOULD BE WELL OVER A 70%
POP FROM WHERE IT PRICED AND
PAIRED SHARES, 3.5 MILLION AT
THIS POINT.
LET ME TOSS IT OVER TO BERTHA IN
THE CROWD WITH THE ZOOM FOLKS
AND WHAT'S GOING ON, HOW FAR WE
ARE FROM OPENING, BERTHA
>> WE'RE GETTING VERY CLOSE.
THERE IS STILL INTEREST COMING
IN AND GENERALLY THEY WANT THE
BOOK TO STABILIZE BEFORE THEY GO
AHEAD AND OPEN.
THEY'VE HAD A LOT OF INTEREST
THAT HAS CONTINUED TO BUILD ALL
MORNING.
WE'VE ALREADY PAIRED OVER
3.5 MILLION SHARES.
IT LOOKS LIKE THEY'LL PROBABLY
GET TO 4 MILLION BEFORE THEY
OPEN HERE BUT IT DOES APPEAR TO
BE IMMINENT HERE.
WE ARE WITHIN THE TWO-MINUTE
WARNING AT THE MOMENT.
WE'RE WATCHING THE SITUATION.
JAY HELLER, THE HEAD OF MARKET
OPERATIONS HERE IS COMMUNICATING
WITH ALL OF THE FOLKS HERE AS
WELL AS THE DIFFERENT TRADING
DESKS ABOUT WHERE WE ARE AT THE
MOMENT AND WE'RE VERY, VERY
CLOSE.
THE COMPANY PRICED AT $36 A
SHARE WHICH GAVE THEM A
VALUATION OF $9 BILLION OR SO
AND THEY ARE LOOKING TO OPEN
HERE WELL ABOVE THAT VALUATION
NORTH OF $16 BILLION RIGHT NOW
IT LOOKS LIKE PERHAPS 70% POP OR
MORE BUT AGAIN THIS IS ONE OF
THOSE THINGS THAT IS MORE ART
THAN SCIENCE AS THEY TRY TO PAIR
THINGS OFF SO THAT YOU DON'T
HAVE AN UNSTABLE OPENING.
BACK OVER TO YOU GUYS.
>> JON, I THINK YOU'RE STILL
WITH US.
BERTHA JUST SAID IT.
YOU DO THE MATH ON 268 MILLION
FULLY DILUTED SHARES AND THAT
PRICE IS 63 YOU'RE GETTING CLOSE
TO $17 BILLION MARKET CAP ON A
COMPANY THAT DID 330 MILLION IN
REVENUES IN LAST YEAR.
THOSE MULTIPLES ARE GETTING
AWFULLY STEEP, AREN'T THEY
>> QUITE A MULTIPLE OF REVENUE
AS YOU MENTIONED, DAVID.
HERE'S A COMPANY TO PUT THIS IN
CONTEXT THAT IS COMPETING IN
BUSINESS AND ENTERPRISE
COMMUNICATION WITH MICROSOFT,
WITH CISCO, WITH GOOGLE, WITH
ADOBE AND HAS BEEN DOING IT
WELL, GROWING AT MORE THAN 100%
A YEAR, ALSO DOING -- MANAGE TO
GO MAKE A PROFIT IN RECENT
QUARTERS AS WELL.
SO THAT COMBINATION OF REALLY
FAST GROWTH, MANAGING
PROFITABILITY AT THE SAME TIME
AND AT THE SAME TIME ON GLASS
D
GLASSDOOR MANAGED TO BE THE MOST
POPULAR CEO ON GLASS DDOOR IN
2018.
SO QUITE A MIX THERE.
CARL
>> JON, THANK YOU.
>>> WE ARE SIMILARLY GET TO GO A
PRETTY CLOSE POINT ON PINS.
BOB PISANI BACK AT POST EIGHT,
BOB?
>> Reporter: GETTING A LOT
CLOSER HERE GUYS WHEN WE GET A
LOT OF PEOPLE HERE IN THE BOOTH.
I'M BACK OVER HERE.
WE'RE GETTING TENSE
NEGOTIATIONS.
STILL 23.25, 23.75.
REMEMBER HOW FAR WE HAVE COME
HERE, 15 TO 17 PRICING AT $19
AND NOW LOOKING SOME WHERE IN
THE $23 RANGE.
STACEY HAD A VERY GOOD POINT,
WHAT THEY'RE REALLY INTERESTED
IN IS A LOT OF SMALLER COMPANIES
COMING IN.
WE HAD ONE TODAY.
DIDN'T GET A LOT OF ATTENTION.
A BIG MINERAL COMPANY.
THEY PRICED AT $18.
THEY OPENED AT $20 AND HERE'S
ANOTHER SUCCESSFUL IPO.
WHILE LYFT IS THE EXCEPTION,
MOST OF THE BIG IPOs THAT HAVE
COME SINCE LEVI STRAUSS HAVE
BEEN SUCCESSFUL.
JU MIA HAD A HUGE IPO.
PAGERDUTY, LEVI STRAUSS ALSO UP
ABOUT 40%.
SO SO FAR THE EARLY INDICATIONS
THE IPO FLOOD WITH THE EXCEPTION
OF LYFT TREMENDOUSLY SUCCESSFUL,
BRINGHAM TODAY.
WE'RE TRYING TO GET AROUND TO
THE CORNER THERE, THEY'RE
ENGAGED IN FAIRLY TENSE
NEGOTIATIONS SO I WON'T GO OVER
THERE AND BOTHER THEM.
I THINK WE'RE GETTING MUCH, MUCH
CLOSER.
WHEN YOU GET CLOSE AND THEY SAY
WE'RE FIVE MINUTES AWAY AND A
RUSH OF EITHER BUYERS OR SELLERS
WILL COME IN WHO ARE DECIDED,
OKAY, IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE IT'S
GOING TO MOVE ANY MORE I'M
PUTTING MY FINAL BID OR OFFER
IN.
IT IS A DYNAMIC AUCTION AND WHEN
PEOPLE THINK THINGS ARE IN
FINALLY, THAT'S WHEN THEY SHOW
THEIR HAND.
IT'S STILL A FLUID SITUATION.
BACK SOON.
>> BOB, IT'S OBVIOUSLY EARLY
WITH THESE THINGS HAVE NOT EVEN
OPENED YET, ARE WE STARTING IN
YOUR MIND TO A RACE THAT NASTY
TASTE OF LYFT'S DECLINE AFTER
ITS OPENING DAY?
>> PINTEREST IS GOING TO BE THE
TEST HERE.
REMEMBER, LYFT WAS 50% ABOVE THE
LAST VALUATION.
PINTEREST INITIALLY LOOKED LIKE
IT WAS ABOUT 25% BELOW --
>> LET ME STOP YOU AND LET'S GET
TO BERTHA COOMBS.
>> OPENED.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Reporter: GUYS, ZOOM IS NOW
OPEN HERE AT $65 EVEN AS THEY
HAVE TREMENDOUS INTEREST STILL
COMING IN AT THE END OVER ALL
THIS STOCK PRICE $36 A SHARE
THAT WAS WELL ABOVE THE UPWARD
RANGE ALSO AN UPWARD OFFERING AS
WELL, TREMENDOUS INTEREST IN
THIS IPO THIS MORNING.
PINTEREST NOT QUITE YET OPEN BUT
ZOOM HAVING A STRONG DEBUT.
JON FORTT IS OVER ON THE OTHER
SIDE AND HAS A LITTLE MORE HERE,
JON.
>> YES.
I CAN SEE THE CEO FROM WHERE I
AM, HE WANT STANDING OVER THERE
IN THE THRONG WATCHING THE BOOK
BUILD, HE WAS OVER HAVING
CONVERSATION INTERESTINGLY WITH
A SMALL GROUP OF PEOPLE.
HE HAS BEEN FOCUSED ON THE
CULTURE OF THIS COMPANY AS WELL
AS ON THE GROWTH.
IT'LL BE INTERESTING TO SEE HOW
HE PUTS INTO CONTEXT THIS HUGE
OPENING THAT THEY'VE HAD, OF
COURSE, THEY'VE PRICED ABOVE THE
RANGE AND THAT PRICE, 36 HAVE
BEEN BLOWN OUT FROM WHERE IT'S
OPENED.
TRADING AT $64 A SHARE JUST
ABOVE THERE AND IT'S
INTERESTING, WE'RE WAITING FOR
PINTEREST TO OPEN AT THE SAME
TIME.
ZOOM WASN'T SEEN IN THE SAME
CONTEXT BECAUSE IT'S NOT A
CONSUMER FACING COMPANY.
IT'S DEALING WITH SMALL BUSINESS
AND ENTERPRISE, IT'S
COMMUNICATIONS PLATFORM.
IT'S A COMPANY COMPETING WITH
THE LIKES OF MICROSOFT, CISCO,
ADOBE, GOOGLE, DOING WELL AT IT
UNDER THE RADAR FOR A WHILE BUT
NOT ANY MORE AS YOU CAN SEE,
THIS STOCK IS UP 78% FROM IT'S
WHERE IT PRICED, GUYS?
>> WE MENTION IT HAD LAST HOUR
AS WELL, BUT THEIR LAST FUNDING
ROUND BACK IN 2017, A BILLION
DOLLARS AND THEN YOU LOOK AT
THIS DEBUT RIGHT NOW, UP 76%.
TICK
TICKER SYMBOL, ZM, MY GOSH, WHAT
A DIFFERENCE A YEAR HAS MADE.
>> Reporter: IT LOOKED LIKE IT
WAS GOING TO BE UNDER THAT AT
$10 BILLION.
HERE'S ONE.
LAST PRIVATE VALUATION, 1 BLD.
YOU'VE GOT TO DO THE MATH.
IT'S PROBABLY AROUND 17 TIMES
IT'S LAST PRIVATE VALUATION, NOT
TO MENTION THE REVENUE MOST
RECENT, 12 MONTHS, FOUR QUARTERS
WORTH OF REVENUE, HAD IT AROUND
335 MILLION IN REVENUE, QUITE A
MULTIPLE WHERE IT IS TRADING
RIGHT NOW.
IT SHOWS WHAT INVESTORS FEEL
ABOUT NOT ONLY GROWTH BUT ALSO
PROFITABILITY, CARL?
>> ALL RIGHT, JON, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
>>> LET'S TAKE STOCK OF WHAT WE
KNOW SO FAR OF LESLIE PICKER
WITH THIS AT POST NINE.
CLEARLY, INVESTORS HUNGRY FOR
SECULAR GROWTH.
>> I WAS SPEAKING WITH SOURCES
YESTERDAY WHO WERE KIND OF --
THEY SAID THEY HAD ENOUGH DEMAND
THAT THEY COULD PRICE THIS THING
AT 40.
WANTED TO BE CONSERVATIVE,
PRICED IT AT 36 AND NOW YOU SEE
THIS 75% POP AS OF RIGHT NOW ON
ITS FIRST DAY OF TRADING.
I WANT TO HONE IN ON HOW RARE
THIS IS.
THEY'RE NOT DOUBLING SHARES ON
THE FIRST DAY OF TRADING.
WE SEE MAYBE ONE IPO A YEAR
DOUBLE THEIR STOCK ON THE FIRST
DAY OF TRADING.
THIS IS PRETTY REMARKABLE IN
TERMS OF FIRST DAY PERFORMANCE.
NOW, IT IS WORTH NOTING THAT
STUDIES HAVE FOUND THAT OFTEN
TIMES WHEN IPOs COME IN SUPER
HOT ON THE FIRST DAY OF TRADING
IT CAN -- IT CAN BE DETRIMENTAL
FOR THEIR LONGER RUN
PERFORMANCE.
I'M NOT SAYING THAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN HERE BUT IN THE PAST --
>> THERE'S PINTEREST.
BOB PISANI, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
>> Reporter: 23.75.
23.75.
PINTEREST GOES PUBLIC AT
10.6 MILLION SHARES.
THAT'S A VERY GOOD NUMBER.
75 MILLION SHARES IS WHAT IS
BEING SOLD TO THE PUBLIC.
YOU SAW IT MORE IN 10% THE
AMOUNT BEING OFFERED RIGHT ON
THE TOP HERE.
THERE'S THE POST OVER THERE AND,
OF COURSE, A LOT OF HAND
CLAPPING AND CHEERING HERE.
REMEMBER THE 15 TO 17 WAS THE
INITIAL PRICING.
PRICE TALK WENT TO $19 AND
OPENED AT $23.75.
YOU SAW WHAT HAPPENED WITH ZOOM
OPENING AT 65, INITIAL TALK
THERE WAS 28 TO 32 JUST A WEEK
AGO.
THREE SUCCESSFUL IPOs JOINING
THE PARADE THAT WE'VE HAD IN THE
LAST FEW WEEKS INCLUDING JUMIA,
ALL STRAYEDING UP 30 OR 40 OR
50% THE SOLE EXCEPTION LYFT DOWN
ABOUT 20%.
BACK TO YOU.
SUCCESSFUL MORNING.
>> CERTAINLY, BOB.
LESLIE, WHETHER YOU'RE
LOOKING -- WHEN YOU LOOK AT A
NAME LIKE PINTEREST WHICH TICKER
SYMBOL IS PINS, STILL LOSING
MONEY?
I'M GOING TO INTERRUPT MYSELF
AND MIDTHOUGHT HERE AND LET YOU
KNOW WHO WE'RE STARING AT RIGHT
NOW.
THAT'S BEN SILVERMAN, CEO AND
COFOUNDER OF PINTEREST, GOING TO
JOIN US HERE AT POST NINE IN
JUST A FEW MOMENTS AS THIS
COMPANY BEGINS TRADING PUBLICLY.
LESLIE, IT WOULD SEEM LOOKING AT
EITHER ONE OF THESE IPOs TODAY,
PINTEREST IS STILL LOSING MONEY
BUT THOSE LOSSES ARE NARROWING.
IT'S A ONE-TWO IN TERMS OF WHAT
INVESTORS ARE, I GUESS,
APPRECIATING IS AND THAT'S
STRONG REVENUE GROWTH AND EITHER
PROFIT IN THE CASE OF ZOOM OR
MOVING CLOSER TO PROFIT IN THE
CASE OF PINTEREST.
>> EXACTLY.
THEY HAVE TO SEE THAT TREND
TOWARD PROFITABILITY.
THEY HAVE TO SEE IT IN SITE.
THEY DON'T HAVE TO BE PROFITABLE
PER SE.
THEY HAVE TO KNOW THE COMPANY
CAN GET THERE IF IT WANTS TO GET
THERE.
WORTH NOTING WITH PINTEREST THAT
IF YOU LOOK AT ITS ENTERPRISE
VALUE WHICH IS WHAT I'M TOLD IS
APPLES TO APPLES WITH ITS LATEST
PRIVATE SALATION, THIS TRADING
RIGHT HERE BRINGS PINTEREST TO
PARODY WITH ITS LATEST PRIVATE
VALUATION.
WE'VE BEEN TALKING A LOT ABOUT
HOW IT'S INITIAL RANGE WAS BELOW
ITS LATEST PRIVATE VALUATION AND
ABOUT $12 BILLION BACK IN 2017
WITH A 20% OR HIGHER POP TODAY,
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE IT MUCH MORE
IN LINE WITH WHERE IT WAS LAST
VALUED IN THE PRIVATE MARKETS.
>> BOB PISANI, LET'S HEAD BACK
OVER TO YOU AT POST EIGHT?
>> Reporter: I THINK THE
IMPORTANT THING HERE IS, YES,
THEY HAVE LOSSES, BUT FAIRLY
SMALL NUMBERS IN TERMS OF
LOSSES, $50 MILLION OR
$60 MILLION COMPARED TO THEIR
ACTUAL REVENUE BASE IS NOT THAT
BAD.
REMEMBER, WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
WITH LYFT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
$2 BILLION IN REVENUES AND A
$1 BILLION IN LOSSES.
WITH UBER WE'RE TALKING
$11 BILLION IN REVENUE AND
$3 BILLION IN LOSSES.
SO THE AMOUNT OF LOSSES FOR
PINTEREST IS FAIRLY SMALL AND
THERE'S A VERY, VERY CLEAR ROAD
TO PROFITABILITY FOR THAT
COMPANY.
THIS IS ONE OF THE TWO METRICS
IN ADDITION TO THE PRICE THAT
EVERYBODY SEEMS MOST CONCERNED
ABOUT AND I THINK THIS WAS PART
OF THE REASON WE SAW SUCH A
POSITIVE REACTION TO PINTEREST,
WHICH, BY THE WAY, IS SITTING AT
$23.24 RIGHT HERE BEHIND ME.
ESSENTIALLY WHERE WE OPENED AT
$23.75 IS ACTUALLY WHERE WE
OPENED AT.
SO WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A NUMBER
OF SMALLER COMPANIES IN THE NEXT
WEEK.
WE'VE GOT SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT NEXT
THERE'S 230 COMPANIES AS OF TWO
WEEKS AGO THAT ARE ON THE ROSTER
TO GO PUBLIC AND I'M REALLY MORE
INTERESTED IN SOME OF THE
MIDLEVEL TECHNOLOGY COMPANIES
LIKE PAGERDUTY, LIKE SOFTWARE
THAT UNDER VERY HOT SPACES LIKE
CYBERSECURITY.
WE'RE SEEING IMMEW KNOW THERAPY
BIO TECHS COMING IN THE NEXT
THREE, FOUR OR FIVE MONTHS THAT
ARE LITERALLY GOING TO CURE
CANCER.
IT'S ONE OF THE MOST EXCITING
THINGS OUT THERE AND UNLIKE THE
BIOTECH WAVE OF THE 1990s WHERE
HAD A WAVE OF IPO THAT WERE
FRANKLY A BUST TO A LARGE
EXTENT, THESE HAVE TREMENDOUS
POTENTIAL TO CURE ALL SORTS OF
DISEASES THAT ARE OUT THERE.
THIS IS A VERY, VERY EXCITING
TIME TO COVER THE IPO BUSINESS.
IT'S MUCH BIGGER THAN UBER AND
PINTEREST AND YOU WANT TO PAY
ATTENTION TO THOSE SMALLER
COMPANIES HERE.
75 MILLION SHARES IS WHAT THE
COMPANY ACTUALLY SOLD.
THAT'S AROUND 12% OR 13% AROUND
THE ACTUAL FLOAT THAT'S OUT
THERE.
ALREADY 21 MILLION SHARES HAVE
CHANGED HANDS.
IF YOU WANT -- THE FIRST
INDICATION OF A SUCCESSFUL IPO
IS THE PRICE.
WHAT YOU WANT HERE IS YOU WANT A
POP AT THE OPEN, 21% IS A LOT,
BUT 6%, 7%, 8% IS ALWAYS
DESIRABLE, THEN CLOSING, CARL, A
LITTLE BIT HIGHER.
WHEN YOU HAVE THAT, A POP AT THE
OPEN AND CLOSE HIGHER, BOTTOM
LINE IS EVERYBODY MAKES MONEY.
CARL, BACK TO YOU.
>> BOB, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> PINTEREST OPENS FOR TRADE A
FEW MOMENTS AGO.
OPENS AT 23.75.
CURRENTLY JUST SHY -- 23.18.
COFOUNDER AND CEO OF PINTEREST
BEN SILVERMAN IS WITH US AT POST
NINE.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> GIVE INVESTORS A PEAK AT WHAT
THE ROAD SHOW SOUNDED LIKE WHEN
YOU MADE YOUR PITCH?
WHAT WERE THE KEY POINTS
>> WE REALLY FOCUSED ON HOW
PEOPLE USE THE PRODUCTS EVERY
DAY.
WE EXPLAINED TO FOLKS THAT
PEOPLE USE PINTEREST TO GET
INSPIRATION FROM EVERYTHING TO
THE RECIPES THEY COOK AND THE
THINGS THEY PUT IN THEIR HOME.
IT'S NOT A SOCIAL NETWORK.
IT'S ABOUT YOURSELF AND YOUR
DREAMS AND ASPIRATIONS.
>> DOES THAT MEAN THAT HIGH
IMPACT USERS DON'T MATTER IN
WAYS THEY DO FOR PLATFORMS LIKE
TWITTER, FOR EXAMPLE
>> WE CARE A TON ABOUT OUR
USERS, BUT WE REALLY THINK ABOUT
IT UTILITY.
WE WANT PEOPLE TO USE IT TO GET
THINGS DONE IN THEIR LIFE.
WE'RE LESS FOCUSED ON MAKING IT
A PLACE WHERE YOU TALK TO YOUR
FRIENDS OR FOLLOW CELEBRITIES.
>> A NUMBER OF ANALYSTS AHEAD OF
THIS IPO TODAY HAVE COME OUT AND
SAID DESPITE THE FACT THAT I
KNOW PINTEREST HAS BEEN
DISTANCING ITSELF FROM THAT
SOCIAL MEDIA CATEGORY HAVE COME
OUT AND MADE THE ARGUMENT THAT,
BEING CATEGORIZED ALONGSIDE SOME
OF THE SOCIAL MEDIA NAMES COULD
BE A USEFUL BENCH MARK FOR
VALUATION.
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO THAT?
>> WE'RE JUST REALLY FOCUSED ON
MAKING IT CLEAR HOW PEOPLE
ACTUALLY USE THE PRODUCT.
THE REASON WE FOCUS ON THINGS
LIKE INSPIRATION AND PLANNING IN
THE FUTURE IS IT'S THE BEST
REPRESENTATION OF HOW PEOPLE ARE
USING IT EVERY DAY.
>> YOU HAVE A NEW CONSTITUENCY
TODAY AMONGST THE VARIOUS ONES
THAT YOU SERVICE AND THAT WOULD
BE PUBLIC SHAREHOLDERS.
DO YOU -- HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
HOW YOU'RE GOING TO GO ABOUT
CHANGING THE WAY YOU DO YOUR JOB
IF AT ALL GIVING YOU'RE NOW A
PUBLIC COMPANY
>> OUR GOAL IS JUST TO CONTINUE
FOCUSING ON MAKING THE PRODUCT
GREAT OVER THE LONG-TERM AND WE
WANT TO HAVE A GOOD RELATIONSHIP
WITH OUR INVESTORS AND MAKE SURE
THAT THEY UNDERSTAND WHERE WE'RE
HEADED AND THAT WAY I THINK
WE'LL BOTH BE ON THE SAME SIDE
AND IT'LL BE A WIN-WIN FOR
EVERYONE.
>> WE'LL BE FOLLOWING THE
COMPANY FROM HERE ON AS WELL.
WHAT WOULD YOU TELL US SHOULD BE
OUR FOCUS IN TERMS OF THE
PROGRESS THAT YOU'RE MAKING
TOWARDS YOUR GOALS WHEN WE LOOK
AT VARIOUS METRICS AT PINTEREST?
>> YOU KNOW, WHEN I RUN THE
COMPANY AS THE CEO, I ALWAYS
FOCUS ON HOW PEOPLE USE THE
PRODUCT FIRST.
SO WE'RE GOING TO FOCUS ON
CONTINUING TO GROW GLOBALLY.
WE ALSO WANT PINTEREST TO BE A
GREAT PLACE FOR BUSINESSES TO
INSPIRE THE PEOPLE THAT ARE ON
THE PLATFORM.
THOSE ARE THE TWO KEY PLAYERS
AND I WOULD FOCUS ON THOSE.
>> WHICH MEANS WHAT?
WEEKLY USERS, LENGTH OF ENGAGE
>> WE SHARED WITH INVESTORS THAT
WE OFTEN LOOK AT MAUs AS AN
INDICATION OF HOW MANY PEOPLE
ARE USING THE PRODUCT AND WE
LOOK AT THE AVERAGE REVENUE PER
USER.
>> IN TERMS OF BEING ABLE TO
MONETIZE THE USERS' YOU
CURRENTLY HAVE ON THE SITE RIGHT
NOW AND I REALIZE FROM AN
ADVERTISING STANDPOINT THE FOLKS
THAT DO COME AND USE PINTEREST
TEND TO BE READY TO MAKE A
PURCHASE.
YOU ROLLED OUT CATALOGS, MORE
SHOPPING FEATURES, BUT LONGER
TERM WHAT DOES THAT -- I GUESS
WHAT DOES THAT PRODUCING
OPPORTUNITY LOOK LIKE ON THE
PLATFORM
>> THE REALLY COOL THING ABOUT
ADVERTISING ON PINTEREST IS THAT
PEOPLE ARE THERE TO GET
INSPIRATION AND DO THINGS AND
THAT OFTEN MEANS BUYING.
SO OVER THE LAST COUPLE YEARS
AND FOR THE FORESEEABLE FUTURE
WE'LL WORK ON BRIDGING THAT GAP
BETWEEN SEEING SOMETHING
INSPIRATIONAL AND FINDING A
PRODUCT FROM A RETAILER THAT YOU
TRUST AT A PRICE POINT THAT
MAKES SENSE FOR YOU.
>> YOU GUYS HAD VIABLE PINS NOT
LONG AGO BUYING THE ABILITY TO
BUY WAS MORE INTEGRATED IN
PINTEREST AND INTERESTINGLY YOU
GUYS STEPPED BACK FROM THAT.
TELL ME WHAT WAS THE THINKING
BEHIND THAT.
WHAT IS IT THAT SAY ABOUT YOUR
STRATEGY, WHAT'S IMPORTANT AND
WHAT'S NOT IMPORTANT
>> WE THINK THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING FROM A USERS' PERSPECTIVE,
THEY CAN GO FROM INSPIRATION TO
ACTION.
WE'RE FOCUSED ON MATCHING THOSE
INSPIRATIONAL IMAGES WITH
PRODUCTS THAT ARE INSIDE THOSE
IMAGES AND DOING IT FROM A BUNCH
OF DIFFERENT RETAILERS AND
THAT'S OUR FOCUS RIGHT NOW.
I THINK TRANSACTIONS, THOSE MAY
COME OUT IN THE FUTURE BUT WE
DON'T HAVE ANY PLANS TO RELEASE
THAT RIGHT NOW.
>> HUGE DEBATE SWIRLING ABOUT
DIFFERENT CLASSES OF STOCK ON
NEW ISSUES AND THE DIFFERENCES
IN VOTING RIGHTS.
WHY DO THAT THIS TIME?
WHY THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
B & A?
>> WE WANT TO MAKE SURE WE'RE
RUNNING THE COMPANY FOR A
LONG-TERM AND --
>> ARE YOU WORRIED THAT THE
PUBLIC MIGHT HAVE OR
INSTITUTIONS COMING IN TO THE
ISSUE WOULD HAVE DIFFERENT IDEAS
ABOUT HOW TO RUN IT THAN YOU
WOULD?
>> I THINK FOR THE MOST PART
THERE SHOULD BE GREAT ALIGNMENT
BUT I DEFINITELY TRUST -- KNOW
WHERE WE WANT TO TAKE IT IN THE
FUTURE.
>> WHEN YOU FIRST HELPED FOUND
THE COMPANY, WHAT WAS YOUR IDEA?
WHAT WAS YOUR INTENT
WHAT NEED DID YOU THINK YOU WERE
GOING TO FILL?
>> AT THE VERY BEGINNING WHAT WE
NOTICED THERE WAS A LOT OF
PEOPLE THAT COLLECT THINGS AND
COLLECTIONS SAY A LOT ABOUT WHO
YOU ARE.
I USED TO COLLECT BUGS AS A KID
WHICH I DIDN'T THINK WOULD
FOLLOW ME INTO ADULTHOOD, BUT IT
DID.
>> BUGS?
>> BUGS.
IT'S AN AMAZING WAY TO DISCOVER
THINGS THAT YOU MIGHT NOT HAVE
EVER SEEN BEFORE.
>> WAS THERE -- IN TERMS OF THE
COMPANIES, THE BRAND NAMES THAT
PLAY ON IT NOW, RIGHT, AND HAVE
INTEREST IN WORKING WITH PEOPLE
WITH FOLLOWERS, WAS THERE A
PATIENT ZERO, ONE THAT PUT YOU
ON THE MAP AS FAR AS YOU WERE
CONCERNED?
>> IT'S BEEN A LITTLE BIT MORE
OF A SLOW AND STEADY PROGRESS.
WHERE WE STARTED WAS WITH
BUSINESSES THAT WERE REALLY
ALIGNED WITH WHAT PEOPLE WERE
DOING.
A LOT OF FOLKS IN RETAIL, A LOT
OF FOLKS IN CONSUMER PRODUCTS
GOODS.
OVER THE LAST YEAR OR SO WE
STARTED TO EXPAND THAT BOTH TO
NEW DIFFERENT TYPES OF
ADVERTISERS AND ALSO
INTERNATIONALLY WHERE ABOUT
TWO-THIRDS OF OUR USERS ARE
TODAY.
>> TALK ABOUT THE INTERNATIONAL
OPPORTUNITY IN TERMS OF THE
REVENUE GROWTH THAT YOU EXPECT
THERE.
IS THERE A CULTURAL DIFFERENCE
IN THE WAY PEOPLE USE IT
WHAT'S YOUR APPROACH THERE GIVEN
INTERNATIONAL IS AN IMPORTANT
PART OF THE GROWTH OPPORTUNITY
THAT CERTAINLY INVESTORS SEE FOR
THE COMPANY?
>> THE FUNNY THING IS PEOPLE ARE
A LOT MORE THE SAME THAN THEY
ARE DIFFERENT.
HERE IN THE U.S., PEOPLE LOVE TO
USE PINTEREST FOR THE FOOD THEY
EAT, FOR DECORATING, FORGETTING
INSPIRATION.
WE SEE THE SAME THING
INTERNATIONALLY.
NOW THE CONTENT IS DIFFERENT.
FOLKS IN FRANCE, THEY WANT
FRENCH RESPIES.
THEY DON'T WANT AMERICAN
CASSEROLES, SO THERE'S WORK WE
DO TO MAKE SURE THE CONTENT
FEELS RELEVANT.
>> WHEN WE GOT TOGETHER A FEW
WEEKS AGO YOU INDICATED I THINK
THAT YOU MAKE VISITS TO PEOPLES'
HOMES.
IS THAT RIGHT?
ARE YOU STILL DOING THAT
DO YOU STILL ANTICIPATE DOING
THAT
AND WHY DO YOU DO THAT
>> THE MOST IMPORTANT THING FOR
A CONSUMER COMPANY IS TO MAKE
SURE THEY REALLY UNDERSTAND THE
NEEDS OF THE PEOPLE THAT ARE
USING IT AND MAYBE THE NEEDS OF
THE PEOPLE THAT HAVEN'T STARTED
USING IT YET.
ME AND MY COFOUNDER, EVAN, WE
MAKE A HABIT OF GOING TO A FEW
CITIES, IT'S NOT A PRESS TOUR
AND WE JUST SIT DOWN WITH PEOPLE
IN THEIR HOMES TO FIND OUT HOW
PINTEREST IS FITTING IN THEIR
LIVES.
>> THIS IS JUST A BREWING DEBATE
LAWMAKERS, ADVERTISERS, SOCIETY
AT LARGE IN TERMS OF
MISINFORMATION AND HOW TECH
COMPANIES AND PLATFORMS LIKE
YOURS ARE ADDRESSING IT.
HOW DO YOU THINK ABOUT THAT AND
I GUESS HOW DO YOU STAY
PROACTIVE ABOUT THAT WHEN
SOMETHING LIKE ANTIVACCINATION
INFORMATION JUST SEEMS TO BE
WHACK-A-MOLE
>> PROVIDING INSPIRATION HIGH
QUALITY CONTENT IS INCREDIBLY
IMPORTANT.
ON ANTIVACCINATION, WE'RE NOT
THE BEST PLACE TO GET MEDICAL
INFORMATION SO IT'S NOT OUR
RESPONSIBILITY TO BE SERVING
THINGS UP SO WE PUT A PAUSE ON
THAT.
WE DON'T CLAIM TO BE A FREE
SPEECH PLATFORM OR A PLACE WHERE
ANYONE CAN PUBLISH ANYTHING.
IT'S ALWAYS ONGOING.
IT'S NOT A ONE AND DONE THING.
>> WE ARE IN A CHAPTER WHERE
WE'RE ON HEIGHTENED ALERT FOR
THINGS LIKE TECH REGULATION IN
THIS COUNTRY, CERTAINLY IN
EUROPE AND COUNTRIES LIKE
AUSTRALIA FOR THINGS LIKE
OFFENSIVE CONTENT AND PRIVACY
BREACHES AND SO FORTH, DOES
PINTEREST SEE THEMSELVES AS
IMMUNED TO WHATEVER REGULATION
MAY COME DOWN THE LINE
>> I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT
REGULATIONS IS COMING DOWN THE
LINE.
>> WE'D ALL LIKE TO KNOW.
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF CHANGES
HAPPENING AND IN GENERAL, A LOT
OF CHANGES ARE HAPPENING FOR THE
BETTER.
PEOPLE LIKE PINTEREST -- LIKE WE
TOUCHED LITERALLY HUNDREDS OF
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE AND SO WE
WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT OUR
PLATFORM IS ACTING RESPONSIBLY
AND IN THE BROADER INDUSTRY THAT
FEELING IN GENERAL IS SHARED.
>> HAVE YOU HAD TO ADD STAFF OR
GUARD RAILS THAT MANAGE CONTENT
OR KEEP CONTENT IN A CERTAIN
LANE
>> WE'VE ALWAYS HAD FOLKS THAT
FOCUS ON CONTENT SAFE AND WE
PLAN TO CONTINUE DOING THAT.
IT'S JUST PART OF THE TERRITORY.
IT'S NOT A ONE AND DONE THING.
IT'S AN ONGOING INVESTMENT
THAT'S ALWAYS GOING TO MATTER.
>> WE'RE WATCHING YOUR STOCK HIT
I THINK NEW HIGHS, UP 29%.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IN TERMS OF
WHERE IT WAS PRICED AND WHERE
IT'S TRADING RIGHT NOW
>> YOU KNOW, I REALLY AM JUST
FOCUSED ON WHERE IT GOES
LONG-TERM.
WE'RE DLIEDED THAT THE OPENING'S
HAPPENING AND IT'S A FUN
MILESTONE.
WE'RE NOT OVERLY FIXATED ON THE
DAY-TO-DAY MOVEMENTS.
>> AS YOU SHOULDN'T BE.
TO BE FAIR WHILE PEOPLE HAVE
CERTAINLY LOOKED AT YOU AND SAY
YOU'RE A FOUNDER, TODAY ON PAPER
YOU'RE WORTH AN ENORMOUS AMOUNT
OF MONEY, DOES IT CHANGE THE WAY
YOU THINK ABOUT THERMZ AT ALL
AND YOUR APPROACH DAY-TO-DAY
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
PINTEREST FROM THE START WAS A
PRODUCT THAT MANY OF MY
COFOUNDERS WANTED TO MAKE FIRST
FOR OUFRZ AND THEN FOR ALL THE
PEOPLE THAT USE IT AND THAT'S
ALWAYS BEEN THE DRIVING
MOTIVATION BEHIND T.
WE'RE REALLY JUST EXCITED THAT
NOW THAT WE'RE A PUBLICLY TRADED
COMPANY WE HAVE MORE RESOURCES
THAT WILL ENABLE DOUSE THAT AND
WE'RE EXCITED ABOUT THE FUTURE.
>> WAS THERE EVER A DEBATE ABOUT
WHETHER YOU WOULD GO PUBLIC ONE
DAY IF YOU COULD
WERE YOU A PROPONENT OF THAT
FROM THE BEGINNING
>> I DON'T THINK WE EVER
CONTEMPLATED THAT IN THE
BEGINNING.
IT'S SURREAL TO BE HERE AT THE
NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE.
WE'RE JUST APPRECIATIVE OF THE
OPPORTUNITY AND EXCITED ABOUT
THE FUTURE.
>> LAST THING I HAVE TO ASK YOU,
PAST OR PROFITABILITY,
EXPECTATIONS OR TARGETS
INVESTORS SHOULD BE WATCHING FOR
THE NEXT COUPLE OF YEARS
>> OVER THE LAST COUPLE YEARS,
I'M EXCITED THE BUSINESS HAS
MADE A TON OF PROGRESS.
WE'VE BUILT OUT THE AD BUSINESS.
WE PLAN TO CONTINUE OPERATING IT
THAT WAY.
>> WE MENTIONED EARLIER THAT WE
SAW YOU ON CODE CONFERENCE TWO
SUMMERS AGO MAYBE.
>> MAYBE THREE.
>> TIME FLIES, BUT YOU HAVE NOT
BEEN, I WOULD ARGUE, WIDELY
PUBLIC IN YOUR APPEARANCES.
ARE WE GOING TO SEE MORE OF YOU?
ARE YOU PREPARED FOR THAT
COMPONENT OF LEADING THE
COMPANY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'LL HAVE TO FIND OUT.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO COME BACK
HERE, FOR EXAMPLE?
>> I'LL PROBABLY COME BACK.
I AM PRETTY FOCUSED ON OUR USERS
AND THE PRODUCT.
I THINK THAT'S APPROPRIATE FOR
THE COMPANY.
>> WE HOPE YOU'LL COME BACK.
>> THANK YOU.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANKS.
>> BEN SILVERMAN OF PINTEREST.
I THINK WE'RE GOING TO SWITCH
OUR FOCUS TO ZOOM, AM I RIGHT
ABOUT THAT
WHICH, OF COURSE, OPENED AT THE
NASDAQ TODAY.
OPENING TRADE OF 65.
JON FORTT'S GOT THAT.
>> I AM HERE AT THE NASDAQ WHERE
ZOOM OPENED FOR TRADE JUST
MINUTES AGO, QUITE A POP.
RIGHT NOW IT IS UP ABOUT 75%
FROM WHERE IT PRICED AND I'M
WITH FOUNDER AND CEO ERIC YUAN,
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> A COUPLE YEARS AGO PINTEREST
WAS VALUED RIGHT AROUND WHERE IT
IS NOW AROUND $12 BILLION.
YOU WERE LESS THAN A BILLION
DOLLARS.
TODAY THE PUBLIC MARKETS HAVE
GIVEN YOU A VALUATION HIGHER NAN
THEIRS, ARE YOU SURPRISED?
>> YES, I'M VERY SURPRISED.
OUR HARD WORK -- WE NEVER
THOUGHT ABOUT THIS AS A PRICE
BUT, AGAIN, WE ARE PRICE IS OUT
OF OUR CONTROL.
>> YOU SAID THAT YOU COULD HAVE
MADE GROWN FASTER, CERTAINLY
GROWN YOUR WORKFORCE FASTER BUT
YOU'VE BEEN CAREFUL OF THE
CULTURE, YOU'VE ALSO MANAGED TO
BE PROFITABLE.
RIGHT NOW INVESTORS CLEARLY
EXPECT A BREAK NECK PACE OF
GROWTH FROM YOU, WHAT DOES THIS
IPO DO TO THE WAY YOU LOOK AT
GROWTH
>> I THINK, FIRST OF ALL, WE
STARTED FROM S&P CUSTOMERS.
WE REALLY WANT TO HAVE OUR --
REALLY HELP OUR COMPANY BRAND.
WITH THAT, OUR ENTERPRISE WILL
TAKE OFF FROM HERE.
>> HOW DETERMINED ARE YOU TO
REMAIN INDEPENDENT
>> I THINK REALLY BOILS DOWN TO
OUR EMPLOYEES.
I ALWAYS TOLD OUR EMPLOYEES, IF
YOU'RE VERY HAPPY AND DO ALL YOU
BEING, I THINK WE'LL BE OKAY.
>> ENTERPRISES USE TO CHART HOW
SUCCESSFUL THEY ARE, YOU GUYS
SCORED PRETTY HIGH BUT YOU'RE UP
AGAINST THE LIKES OF CISCO.
>> YEP.
>> MICROSOFT, ADOBE, ET CETERA.
HOW DO YOU LOOK AT BIG COMPANY
COMPETITION, WHAT'S GOING TO
CONTINUE TO GIVE YOU AN EDGE NOW
THAT YOU'RE PUBLICLY TRADED?
>> THOSE COMPANIES ARE ALL GREAT
COMPANIES.
I ADMIRE THEM A LOT.
MOST OF TIME WE DO NOT SPEND,
YOU KNOW, LOOKING AT
COMPETITORS.
WE SPEND TIME TO CARE ABOUT OUR
CUSTOMERS.
WE WANT TO UNDERSTAND WHAT'S THE
PINPOINT FROM A CUSTOMER SIDE.
WE WANT TO BE THE FIRST COMPANY
TO UNDERSTAND THE CUSTOMER'S
PINPOINT.
TO COME UP WITH A SOLUTION TO
TAKE CARE OF THE CUSTOMER.
IF WE KEEP DOING, THAT THE
CUSTOMERS WILL TRUST US.
WE DO ALL WE CAN TO MAKE SURE
OUR CUSTOMER HAPPY.
>> I BELIEVE ABOUT 18% OF YOUR
BUSINESS IS INTERNATIONAL AT
THIS POINT, IS THAT RIGHT?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> IF YOU'RE GOING TO GROW, A
LOT THAT HAVE GROWTH IS GOING TO
HAVE TO COME INTERNATIONALLY.
DOES THE PREMIUM MODEL YOU'VE
HAD WORK AS WELL OUTSIDE THE
U.S. AS IT HAS INSIDE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
ANYWHERE FROM JAPAN, EUROPE,
JUST GO TO OUR WEBSITE AND FOR
THE BIG ENTERPRISE CUSTOMERS,
OUR REPS CAN TALK WITH THEM.
THERE'S NO LIMITATION IN TERMS
OF WHERE WE SHOULD OFFER OUR
SERVICE.
ANYWHERE YOU CAN SUBSCRIBE TO
ZOOM SERVICE.
>> I BELIEVE ABOUT 55% OF THE
334 CUSTOMERS YOU HAVE THAT ARE
PAYING LAST YEAR MORE THAN
$100,000 FOR ZOOM SERVICES, THEY
CAME IN FIRST THROUGH SOME FREE
ACCOUNT.
IS THAT NUMBER GOING TO STAY
THAT HIGH OR DO YOU HAVE TO HIRE
MORE SALES PEOPLE TO FUEL
GROWTH
>> I THINK IT'LL BE HIGHER.
TO BE A PUBLIC COMPANY, MORE
BRAND AWARENESS, WORKING HARDER.
I THINK THAT NUMBER WILL BE MUCH
HIGHER DOWN THE ROAD.
>> WHY IT SALES FORCE TOSS IN
$100 MILLION
>> WE REALLY WANTED TO EMBED
ZOOM IN OUR BUSINESS
APPLICATIONS.
THAT'S WHY WE -- ALL THE REPS
LIVE ON PLATFORM TO HAVE MUCH
BETTER INTEGRATION BETWEEN ZOOM.
I THINK THAT'S A NEW BRAND FOR
US TO WORK THEM ALL CLOSELY.
>> WHAT HAPPENS WHEN THE ECONOMY
TURNS DOWN
WHEN THEY'RE MAKING MONEY, WHEN
THERE'S MONEY TO GO AFTER, SPARE
NO EXPENSE TO COORDINATE TO
UNDERSTAND WHAT REGIONS TO GO.
WHEN THE ECONOMY TURNS DOWN AND
IT'S BEEN HOT FOR A DECADE, WHAT
HAPPENS?
>> IF A ECONOMY TURNS DOWN,
GUESS WHAT
NOBODY'S GOING TO TRAVEL ANY
MORE.
EVERYBODY'S GOING TO USE ZOOM.
I THINK IT'S BETTER FOR US.
>> I WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT YOUR
OWN JOURNEY TO THIS POINT.
I'M NOT SURE YOU EXPECTED A FEW
MONTHS AGO NECESSARILY TO BE
MONTHS AGO TO BE A PAPER
BILLIONAIRE, BUT YOU ARE TODAY
WITH THE STOCK DOING WHAT IT'S
DOING.
AND CERTAINLY A FEW YEARS AGO
WHEN YOU WERE LOOKING TO GET
INTO THE U.S., YOUR VISA WAS
DENIED SEVERAL TIMES
>> EIGHT TIMES.
>> WHAT IS YOUR MESSAGE ON THE
DAY YOUR COMPANY IS GOING PUBLIC
TO PEOPLE WHO ARE CRAFTING
POLICY ON IMMIGRATION?
>> I WOULD SAY, YOU KNOW, THE
UNITED STATES IS A GREAT
COUNTRY, AMERICAN DREAM.
I THINK ALL OF THE PATHS IS AN
OPEN CULTURE ON IMMIGRATION CAN
COME HERE.
I THINK IT'S ALWAYS GOOD, AN
OPEN CULTURE TO EMBRACE ALL OF
THE PEOPLE FROM ALL OVER THE
WORLD, DIVERSITY IS ALWAYS GOOD.
I THINK IT IS SUCH A SHORT-TERM
PROBLEM.
I THINK I HAVE A HIGH
CONFIDENCE
I'M VERY OPTIMISTIC.
THIS AMERICAN CULTURE I THINK
WILL LAST FOREVER.
>> YOU HAVE A VIDEO CONFERENCING
PRODUCT WHICH YOU SAID WILL
ALLOW PEOPLE NOT TO NECESSARILY
HAVE TO TRAVEL, YET YOU'RE BASED
IN SAN JOSE.
A CITY I KNOW WELL
I LIVED THERE ABOUT 14 YEARS
IT'S EXPENSIVE THERE
DO YOU STAY IN SILICON VALLEY?
IS IT IMPORTANT TO BE THERE WHEN
TECHNOLOGIES LIKE YOURS ALLOW
YOU TO LIVE ANYWHERE
>> I THINK WITH ZOOM, VIDEO
CONFERENCING YOU CAN LIVE
ANYWHERE WITH ANY DEVICE, TALK
WITH CUSTOMERS AND PARTNERS.
THERE ARE SO MANY DIFFERENT
COMPANIES -- WHEN WE STARTED
MANY YEARS AGO, WE DID NOT HAVE
PHYSICAL OFFICE.
WE LIVED ON ZOOT PLATFORM.
I THINK MUCH BETTER EMPLOYEE
ENGAGEMENT, THE COST, EMPLOYEES
HAVE MORE FLEXIBLE TIME.
I DON'T THINK THERE ARE ANY
ISSUES TO LIVING IN A ZOOM
PLATFORM
CAN YOU LIVE ANYWHERE AND WORK
TOGETHER TODAY.
>> WHAT'S YOUR TAKE ON THE
AMERICAN ECONOMY, NOT ONLY
POWERING YOUR GROWTH RIGHT NOW
BUT HELPING THIS COMPANY BECOME
WHAT IT IS
>> I'M VERY OPTIMISTIC
I THINK AMERICA'S ECONOMY WILL
DO BETTER AND BETTER IN THE
FUTURE
IT'S A GREAT CULTURE, OPEN
CULTURE.
EVERYBODY'S WORKING VERY HARD.
I THINK BRIGHT FUTURE AHEAD OF
US.
>> ERIC YUAN, FOUNDER AND CEO OF
ZOOM
I WILL MAKE THE IS LONG REACH
AND SHAKE YOUR HAND.
BIG DAY FOR YOU AND IPOs IN
GENERAL.
CONGRATULATIONS.
BACK TO YOU.
>> JOHN, TO THAT POINT THE OTHER
BIG DEBUT HAS BEEN PINTEREST
THAT'S A NICE SPLIT SCREEN OF
THE TWO BIG ISSUES TODAY
BOTH CONTINUING TO SURGE IN
EARLY TRADING.
PINTEREST'S CEO DID SKPLOIN US A
FEW MOMENTS AGO AND EXPLAIN WHAT
THAT MEANS FOR ALL INVESTORS.
>> OUR GOAL IS FOCUS ON MAKING
THE PRODUCT GREAT IN THE LONG
TERM AND HAVE A GOOD
RELATIONSHIP WITH OUR INVESTORS
AND MAKE SURE THEY UNDERSTAND
WHERE WE'RE HEADED AND I THINK
WE WILL BOTH BE ON THE SAME SIDE
AND WIN-WIN FOR EVERYONE.
>> INTERESTING TO HEAR HIM
RESPONDING ABOUT ANTI-VAX,
SAYING WE'RE NOT A FREE SPEECH
FORUM.
>> WE GO BACK TO THE ARGUMENT
AND POINT PINTEREST IS MAKING
THEY'RE NOT A SOCIAL MEDIA
COMPANY AND THEY'RE MUCH MORE
FOCUSED ON ENGAGEMENT AND PINS
AND BASICALLY DRIVING
ADVERTISING REVENUE TIED TO A
USER BASE THAT COMES WITH A VERY
HIGH INTENT TO ACTUALLY MAKE
PURCHASES.
LOOKING AT SHARES OF PINTEREST
UP 27%
INCREDIBLE DAY AT BOTH EXCHANGES
ON THE HEELS OF THIS
I THOUGHT IT WAS INTERESTING IN
OUR CONVERSATION WITH SILBERMANN
WHEN HE SAID HE GOES AND HE
VISITS WITH CONSUMERS AT THEIR
HOUSES TO GET A FEEL WHAT
THEY'RE INTERESTED IN.
>> YES, ZEROED IN ON MAUs AS
METRIC TO WATCH, TALKED ABOUT
DEFENDING QUITE PLAINLY THE DUAL
CLASS STRUCTURE AND THESE
SPECIAL BILLING RIGHTS FOR CLASS
B, WHICH THE PUBLIC IS NOT
BUYING TODAY
LET'S GET BACK TO THE NASDAQ
JOHN FORD, AS WE PAY ATTENTION
TO WHAT HAPPENED OVER THERE
TODAY.
>> THANK YOU, CARL
I'M HERE NOW WITH NASDAQ CEO
DINA FRIEDMAN.
THANK YOU FOR HAVING US HERE.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR BEING
HERE
IT'S BEEN A BIG MORNING.
>> IT'S BEEN A BIG MORNING FOR
IPOs
I THINK ZOOM TURNED OUT BIGGER
THAN A LOT OF PEOPLE EXPECTED.
CLEARLY UP 75% RIGHT NOW
WHAT DOES THE PROCESS LOOK LIKE
FROM WHERE YOU'RE SITTING?
>> I THINK, FIRST, IT COMES DOWN
TO THE COMPANY AND ZOOM AS AN
ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE BUSINESS
DEMONSTRATED THEY CAN GROW, THEY
HAVE RESILIENCY AND LOYALTY
AMONG THEIR CLIENTS.
THEIR SOLUTION IS QUITE STICKY
ONCE IT'S INTEGRATED INTO YOUR
OFFICE AND WORK FLOWS, IT'S A
VERY STICKY BUSINESS
I THINK THEY'VE BEEN ABLE TO
DEMONSTRATE THAT ON THE ROAD AND
DONE A GREAT JOB OF BRINGING IN
INVESTORS.
>> I HAVE TO ASK ABOUT PROCESSES
AGAIN BECAUSE YOU HAD LYFT ABOUT
THREE WEEKS AGO.
THE NASDAQ'S JOB IS MAKE SURE
THINGS OPEN SMOOTHLY
IT DID THAT.
BUT THEN THE PRICE HAS JUST
TANKED, PRICE DISCOVERY WISE
IT'S BEEN THE TALK OF A NUMBER
OF COMPANIES LOOKING TO GO
PUBLIC
WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
>> FIRST OF ALL, WE'RE VERY
PROUD TO HAVE LYFT AS PART OF
OUR LIST OF COMPANIES, AND THEY
ARE GREAT BUSINESS IN AND OF
THEMSELVES
I THINK THEY HAVE A LONG-TERM
VISION
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT INVESTORS
EVALUATE THESE COMPANIES OVER
THE LONG TERM AND THEIR ABILITY
TO EXECUTE ON WHAT THEY DO
DISCUSS WHILE THEY'RE ON THE
ROAD
IT'S VERY EARLY DAYS FOR LYFT.
THEY HAVE A LONG ROAD, NO PUN
INTENDED, TO GO DOWN TO MAKE
SURE THEY'RE EXECUTING ON WHAT
THEIR PLANS ARE.
BUT THEY HAVE BIG PLANS, AND I
THINK THEY'VE DONE A GREAT JOB
OF EXECUTION ACROSS THEIR
BUSINESS SO FAR.
I BELIEVE IT'SREALLY IMPORTANT
TO LOOK AT THEM OVER THE LONG
TERM AND NOT JUST THE LAST FEW
WEEKS.
>> HAS THERE BEEN ANY CHANGE IN
THE WAY YOU COMMUNICATE OR THAT
COMPANIES LOOKING TO IPO HAVE
COMMUNICATED WITH YOU BASED ON
HOW THAT PRICE DISCOVERY PROCESS
HAS GONE ON WITH A COMPANY LIKE
THAT
WHAT ARE YOU TELLING THEM?
WHAT ARE THEY ASKING YOU
>> YES, FIRST OF ALL I DO
BELIEVE MOST COMPANIES
UNDERSTAND EVERY IPO IS ITS OWN
STORY.
THEY LOOK AT THEIR OWN BUSINESS
MODEL, THEY LOOK AT THEIR OWN
ACCESS TO INVESTORS AND CAPITAL,
THE CONVERSATIONS THEY HAD WITH
INVESTORS AND ADVISERS AND THEY
DO RECOGNIZE THAT THEIR STORY
WILL BE ITS OWN MAKING
SO THEY HAVE TO DEMONSTRATE THAT
THEY HAVE A LONG-TERM VIEW
THEY HAVE A LONG-TERM PLAN
I DON'T BELIEVE, QUALIFICATIONS
WITH CLIENTS HAVE NOT CHANGED ON
THE BASIS OF ONE IPO
THEY'RE LOOKING AT THIS OVER THE
LONG TERM TO KNOW THERE'S A
HEALTHY MARKET, HEALTHY DEMAND
OVERALL FOR COMPANIES.
>> HOW HEALTHY IS THE IPO MARKET
RIGHT NOW?
AND DO YOU EXPECT THE
CONVERSATION ABOUT THAT HEALTH
TO SHIFT BASED ON WHAT HAPPENED
HERE TODAY
>> I THINK, FIRST OF ALL, IT'S
BEEN HEALTHY FOR A WHILE
SO WE HAD 118 OOIPOs LAST YEAR D
50 SO FAR THIS YEAR.
IT'S A HEALTHY MARKETPLACE
THERE'S A LOT OF PENT-UP DEMAND
STILL, GIVEN THE COMPANIES THAT
WANT TO COME OUT THIS YEAR
SO I WOULD SAY IT'S BEEN PRETTY
STEADY
WE HAD THAT ONE TIME DURING THE
FOURTH QUARTER THAT PEOPLE GOT A
LITTLENERVOUS ABOUT HOW THINGS
WOULD LOOK GOING INTO '19 AND IT
JUST RECOVERED
SO IT'S BEEN A STRONG
ENVIRONMENT FOR IPOs
AND OBVIOUSLY TODAY IS A GREAT
DAY FOR THE MARKETS IN GENERAL
BUT I THINK IT'S ALSO
REFLECTIVE, AGAIN, OF THE STORY
OF ZOOM AND THE STRENGTH OF
THEIR BUSINESS.
>> SOME YEARS AGO NOT TOO LONG
AGO THERE WAS TALK ABOUT
REGULATION AND LOGGING DOWN THE
IPO MARKET, THAT COMPANIES WERE
NOT GOING TO WANT TO GO PUBLIC
WHAT HAPPENED TO THAT?
>> I ACTUALLY STILL THINK THERE
ARE SOME REAL IMPEDIMENTS TO
COMPANIES WANTING TO TAP THE
PUBLIC MARKETS EARLIER IN THEIR
LIFE CYCLE
THE COMPANIES COMING OUT NOW ARE
MULTI BILLION DOLLAR COMPANIES
THAT WAITS YEARS TO GO PUBLIC.
WHAT WE WANT IS COMPANIES EARLY
IN THEIR LIFE CYCLE TO GIVE MORE
OF THE AVERAGE INVESTORS ACCESS
TO THEIR GROWTH AS THEY'RE
YOUNGER COMPANIES AND NOT
WAITING NECESSARILY UNTIL THEY
BECOME GREAT 10 BILLION
COMPANIES TO TAP THE MARKET.
WE CONTINUE TO SEE IMPEDIMENTS
FOR COMPANIES WANTING TO TAP THE
MARKETS EARLY IN THEIR LIFE
CYCLE.
>> AFTER A DAY LIKE THIS, HOW IS
YOUR CALL VOLUME GOING TO CHANGE
TO EXACTLY THAT POINT, SIZES OF
COMPANIES INTERESTED IN GOING
PUBLIC
>> WE ARE SEEING MORE AND MORE,
PARTICULARLY IN THE ENTERPRISE
SOFTWARE SPACE AND CLOUD SPACE
THERE ARE A LOT OF GREAT
COMPANIES OUT THERE THAT ARE IN
OBVIOUSLY I WOULD SAY $1 BILLION
TO $2 BILLION RANGE THAT ARE
RECOGNIZING THE MARKET IS
WIDE-OPEN FOR THEM
IF THEY CAN DEMONSTRATE
CONSISTENT GROWTH AND SHOW THE
RESILIENCY OF THE BUSINESS MODEL
IN TERMS OF STICKINESS TO THEIR
CLIENTS AND SHOW SCALEABILITY
LIKE ZOOM HAS DONE TO HAVE A
PATH TO PROFITABILITY, I THINK
THEY WILL FIND THEIR MARKET IS
VERY RECEPTIVE.
>> ZOOM WAS $1 BILLION TO $2
BILLION A FEW MONTHS AGO
PROBABLY SOME OF THOSE COMPANIES
HAVE A PHOTO OF ERIC YUAN ON
THEIR MIRROR NOW.
>> THE ABILITY TO GROW IN SUCH A
SHORT PERIOD OF TIME AND GET TO
PROFITABILITY IS WHAT
DISTINGUISHED THEM
>> ADENA FRIEDMAN, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
>>> JOHN, DON'T GO TOO FAR
DOW UP 100 POINTS, S&P BACK TO
IT'S WORTH TAKING A MOMENT TO
FRAME WHAT A MORNING WE'VE HAD
TWO VERY SUCCESSFUL ISSUES AT
LEAST AT THIS POINT BOTH HERE
FOR BOTH EXCHANGES
THE POLITICAL MEDIA CONTINUES TO
DISSECT THE MUELLER REPORT AS
HEADLINES ARE POPPING EVERY FEW
SECONDS HERE
AND THEN IF YOU THINK THAT'S NOT
ENOUGH, NEXT WEEK THE EARNINGS
ARE TRULY -- IT'S THE WEEK, IT'S
MICROSOFT, COKE, CAT, BOEING,
TWITTER, AMAZON, TESLA AND A LOT
MORE.
>> IT IS
AND THERE'S QUITE A NUMBER OF
EARNINGS THIS MORNING AND YOU
CAN SEE THAT IN THE S&P AS WELL.
IT'S LEADING EVERYTHING HIGHER
THE INDUSTRIAL NAMES LIKE THAT
ARE ALL BETTER THAN EXPECTED
BUT QUITE THE HOUR
WHAT IS THE TAKE FROM THE NASDAQ
RIGHT NOW?
>> MORGAN, THIS IS