BATHROOM
IF WE CAN TAKE THE KIDS BASIC
LANGUAGE OF GRAMMAR AND FINANCE,
SAME AS WE -- THEN THEY'RE NOT
AFRAID, NOT TO ASK THE QUESTION,
OR MAKE UP WORDS DURING
SEGMENTS
>> THEY CAN DO THAT, TOO.
>> NAN MORRISON, A GREAT TOPIC.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME HERE
>>> FOR MORE VISIT
CNBC.COM/INVESTINYOU
WE ARE INVESTORS IN ACORNS, WE
SHOULD NOTE.
>>> THAT DOES IT, A LONG
WEEKEND, EVERYBODY, BUT WE'RE
NOT DONE YET
"POWER LUNCH" BEGINS RIGHT NOW.
>> AND I AM INTIMIDIZED.
>> GOOD MORNING.
NEW AT 2:00, THE MUELLER REPORT
IS OUT
THE PRESIDENT DECLARES VICTORY,
EXONERATION, BUT WILL THIS FIGHT
CONTINUE TO HANG OVER HIS
ADMINISTRATION AND MAYBE EVEN
THE MARKETS?
IT'S A HUGE DAY FOR IPOs
SEVERAL OF THEM OF MAJOR
INTEREST, BEGINNING WITH
PINTEREST, AND SHARES OF ZOOM
ARE ZOOMING HIGHER.
>>> PLUS KEVIN O'LEARY IS NOT
HAPPY.
MR. WONDERFUL IS ANGRY
HE'S GOING TO JOIN US TO
COMPLAIN ABOUT GETTING THE
EIGHTH PICK IN THE STOCK DRAFT
SOUNDS LIKE THE NEW YORK KNICKS.
"POWER LUNCH" STARTS RIGHT NOW
♪
>>> WELCOME TO "POWER LUNCH.
I'M COURT ANYTHING REAGAN.
TWO IPOs, BOTH POPPING IN THEIR
DEBUT.
>> HEY THERE, COURT, A REDACTED
VERSION OF THE MUELLER REPORT ON
INTERFERENCE IN THE 2016
ELECTION HAS BEEN RELEASED TO
THE PUBLIC AND THE WHITE HOUSE
EAMON HAS MORE.
>> Reporter: WE'RE LEARNING MORE
AND MORE AS WE GO THROUGH THIS
400-PAGE REPORT BY BY BIT, THAT
THE PRESIDENT ORDERED THE FIRING
OF ROB MUELLER AND IT WAS THE
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL WHO DOESN'T
FOLLOW THAT ORDER, SAYING THAT
WHEN THE PRESIDENT CALL McGANN A
SECOND TIME ON JUNE 17th HE
RECALL HE WAS MORE DIRECT, CALL
ROD, TELL MUELLER HAS CONFLICTS
AND CAN'T BE SPECIAL COUNSEL --
BECAUSE WILLIAM BARR BOO, THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL, SUGGESTED THAT
BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT DIDN'T
TAKE ANY OVERT ACTION TO STOP
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S
INVESTIGATION, IT WOULD BE HARD
TO MAKE THE CASE THAT HE WAS
OBJECT INSTRUCTING JUSTICE
THAT YOU BECAUSE IN THE END THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL WASN'T FIRED
NOW WE'RE LEARNING THAT THE
PRESIDENT DID ORDER THE FIRING,
BUT DON McGAHN DID NOT
SO IT'S POSSIBLY HE PROTECTED
THE PRESIDENT, AND SET UP THE
SITUATION WHERE THE MUELLER
REPORT WAS UNABLE TO COME TO A
CONCLUSION ON OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL IS SAYING
AS A RESULT OF THE PRESIDENT'S
ACTIONS HERE, IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO
MAKE THE CASE THERE WAS ON
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
>> AS THE SPECIAL COUNSEL SAID,
IT WAS DIFFERENT TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT THE PRESIDENT'S INTENT WAS,
BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT DIDN'T SIT
DOWN FOR AN INTERVIEW, BUT HE
DID SAY HE FOUND HIS WRITTEN
ANSWERS INSUFFICIENT I THINK WAS
THE WORD HE USED.
>> Reporter: I THINK THEY ALSO
SAID THEY WERE INADEQUATE.
THE PRESIDENT SUGGESTING A
NUMBER OF TIMES IN THE WRITTEN
ANSWERS HE DIDN'T REMEMBER,
DIDN'T REAL VARIOUS INSTANCES.
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S TEAM
WANTED TO TALK TO THIS
PRESIDENT, HIS LAWYERS DID NOT
WANT THEM TO TALK TO HIM, AND
BECAUSE OF THAT THEY COULDN'T
GET INSIDE THE PRESIDENT'S HEAD.
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL SUGGESTING
THEY WERE SIMPLY OUT OF TIME AND
IT WOULD BE A CONSTITUTIONAL
BATTLE TO FIGHT TO FORCE, TO
ATTEMPT TO FORCE THE PRESIDENT
TO SIT DOWN IN PERSON AND TALK
TO THEM.
HE DECIDED ULTIMATELY NOT TO
PURSUE IT, NOT TO ISSUE THAT
SUBPOENA FOR THE PRESIDENT'S
PERSONAL TESTIMONY
THAT'S PARTS OF, IT WOULD
APPEAR, WHY THIS RECORD ENDED
THE WAY IT DID.
>> EAMON, THANK YOU.
>> YOU BET
>>> A LOT OF READING FOR MANY OF
US THIS WEEKEND TO DO.
MARKETS SHRUGGING OFF THE
MUELLER REPORT, BUT WITH A PAIR
OF HIGH-PROFILE IPOs HITTING THE
TICKER, THERE'S STILL PLENTY TO
CAPTURE THE ATTENTION OF
INVESTORS.
BOB PISANI IS ON THE FLOOR OF
THE NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE.
>> WE'RE ABOUT 10% THROUGH THE
EARNINGS SEASON, BELIEVE IT OR
NOT.
HE'S THE KEYING FOR THE WHOLE
EARNINGS SEASON, BEATS WELL
ABOVE TYPICAL BEATS.
DOVER BEAD BY 12 SPEAKERS,
HONEYWELL BY, TRAVELERS, UNION
PACIFIC.
ON A TYPICAL TIME POLL OF THE
TIME YOU'LL SEE ABOUT 3%
EARNINGS BEATS, AND THEY'RE
BETTER THAT ARE EXPECTED,
BECAUSE ANALYSTS CUT TOO MUCH IN
DECEMBER
ALL OF THESE STOCKS TRADING TO
THE UP SIDE.
THE OTHER STORY TODAY IPOs,
PINTEREST, WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
15 TO $17.
IT OPENS AT 2375
YOU SEE HERE TRADING ABOVE THAT
NUMBER ITSELF.
ZOOM, EVEN BIGGER STORY.
JUST FOUR DAYS AGO WE WERE
TALKING 28 TO 32
WAIT -- THEY PRICE AT 36, IT
OPENS AT 65.
THAT'S NOT A TYPO, AND TRADING
RIGHT AROUND WHERE IT OPENED
SO WHAT'S GOING TO BE NEXT
WE DON'T KNOW, BUT HERE'S SOME
THOUGHTS
APRIL 22nd, IHEART MEDIA COULD
POTENTIALLY ANNOUNCE TERMS
THAT'S ONE OF THE UNICORNS OUT
THERE, AND POTENTIALLY NEXT
FRIDAY, APRIL 26th, UBER COULD
POTENTIAL DO THAT.
MORE LIKELY THE FOLLOWING WEEKS.
TERMS, NOT GOING PUBLIC, BUT
ANNOUNCING WHEN IT MIGHT BE AND
A RANGE OF PRICING
>>> A LOT OF STUFF COMING DOWN
20 IPOs, TYLER, IN THE MONTH OF
MAY, AT LEAST, MAYBE AS MANY AS
>> SUPPLY IS COMING.
ROBERT, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> WEEKLY JOBLESS CLAIMS IN
RETAIL SALES PAINTING A ROSY
PICTURE OF THE U.S. ECONOMIC
STEVE LEASH IESMAN IS HERE WITH
>> A WEAK ECONOMY THAT CAUSED SO
MUCH CONCERN LATE LAST YEAR,
SUDDENLY NOT THAT WEAK
A COMBINATION OF BETTER TRADE
AND RETAIL DATA HAS ECONOMISTS
MARKING IT UP FOR THE FORECAST,
AND DO IT SHARPLY.
AS TILE HER WAS SAYING, GROWTH
AT 2.4%, A LONG WAY FROM THE 1%
FORECAST AS EARLY AS MARCH
IT'S NOT GROWTH LIKE LAST YEAR,
AND CURRENT QUARTER IS FORECAST
TO COME IN RIGHT ABOUT THE SAME.
THERE'S MORE DATA TO COME, AND
SOME ARE CAUTIOUS HERE
RETAIL SALES WERE UP 1.6%.
WE HAD STRENGTH IN ELECTRONICS,
INTERNET SALES, GROCERY STORES
AND CLOTHING, AND JOBLESS CLAIMS
FALLING FOR 192,000, FROM WHAT I
CAN TELL THAT'S THE LOWERS LEVEL
SITS 1969, THERE WERE A LOT
FEWER WORKERS BACK THEN.
SO THE FED LIKELY TO NOT HIKE
RATES, BUT THOSE WHO WERE CUT
THEY WOULD CUT RATES, THEY'LL BE
DISAPPOINTED
AN ECONOMYING RUNNING AT 2.5%
DOESN'T NEED HELP FROM THE
CENTRAL BANK
OWNERSHIP DO QUAINT AT A TIMIVE
EASING AGAIN
WE DON'T NEED TO DO THAT.
>> IF I CAN DO BACK TO THE
RETAIL, CLOTHING UP 2%.
>> WHAT ARE YOU HEARING?
FOR FOLKS TO KNOW, COURTNEY AND
I SIT RELATIVELY CLOSE, WE HAVE
A RUNNING THING ABOUT WHAT SHE
HEARS FROM THE STORIES AND A LOT
OF TIMES THEY CLASH.
WHAT ARE YOU HEARING
>> AGAIN I THINK IT'S
CONFLICTING.
I THINK SOME ARE STRONG, SOME
ARE NOT.
THERE'S STILL AREAS OF WEAKNESS
IN DEPARTMENT STORES
>>> IT'S A COOL THING THAT'S
HAPPENING MAYBE WE WON'T BE
ARGUING, BECAUSE THE DATA WILL
BE THE SAME.
>> TIMES I -- OR AS ZAPPA CALLED
IT, THE --
>>> THE DOW ON PACE TO MOST ITS
THIRD WEEKLY GAIN CAN THE DC
DRAMA DERAIL THE RALLY
JIM, I'M GOING TO ASK A TILER
MATHISEN COMPOUND QUESTION
NOW REAR TRACKING FIRST QUARTER
GDP.
THEY HAD THIS MUELLER REPORT,
WHICH I THINK WE CAN GREAT IS
RELATIVELY BENIGN.
IF WE HAVE A STRONG ECONOMY AND
A PRESIDENT DOESN'T SEEM TO BE
IN ANY SORT OF LEGAL JEOPARDY,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DO YOU THINK THE MARKETS ARE
HAPPY WITH TRUMP
COULD HE BE REELECTED?
IS IT GOOD FOR THE MARKETS GOING
FORWARD?
>> I THINK ON THE TRUMP
QUESTION, THE TIMING OF GROWTH
AND THE CHARACTER OF THE ECONOMY
IS WHAT'S MOST IMPORTANT TO THE
ELECTRIC
IN SOME SENSE WE MAY LOOK BACK
AND SAY THE SLOWDOWN, IF THERE
WAS ONE HERE, IN 2019 MIGHT HAVE
BEEN GREAT TIMING FOR THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY, IN THE SENSE
IF IT SLOWS DOWN AND WE BRING
THE FULL POLICSE
BUTTON, AND WE'LL HAVE TO SEE
HOW MUCH TIME, TO GREG'S POINT
EVEN THOUGH THE ECONOMIC WOULD
YOU FLOWING -- AND BROUGHT IT TO
A PAUSE, SO WE HAD POSSIBLE
EASE
NOW WE'RE JUST ENTERING A PERIOD
WHERE WE'LL HAVE REVIVE AND
GROWTH WITHOUT FED TIGHTENING.
THAT'S PRETTY GOOD, TOO.
I THINK THE TEN-YEAR TREASURY
COULD GO FROM 2.6, AND IT
WOULDN'T HURT STOCKS
AT SOME OF THE POINT THE FED
WILL BE TIGHTENING AGAIN, AND
ULTIMATELY THE FED OVERDOES IT,
BUT THERE'S ANOTHER GOOD PERIOD
WHERE GROWTH ACCELERATES WITHOUT
TIGHTENING THAT I THINK THE
MARKET COULD DO WELL IN AS WELL.
>> I THINK THE KEY THINK IS,
YES, THE FED HIT THE PAW BUTTON.
I THEY'RE DONE FOR A YEAR.
I THINK THAT HELPS RISK ASSETS
IT'S JUST YOU HAVE TO LOOK AT
WHAT DO PEOPLE HATE HERE
I THINK PEOPLE ARE STILL VERY
NEGATIVE
I THINK PEOPLE ARE STILL MORE
CAUTIOUS ABOUT EQUITIES, SO
MAYBE A BET OVERWEIGHT EM.
WHAT WE HAVE HERE, WE HAVE SNNK
BANKS THAT SEEN -- AND SO I I
THINK WITH CENTRAL BANKS RATES
ARE VERY LOW, I THINK THIS IS
THE TIME TO TAKE A RISK HERE
>> WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF LARRY
FISK'S COMMENT, THERE ARE A LOT
OF NONBELIEVERS OUT THERE.
YOU'VE HAD MONEY GOING INTO THE
WRONG PLACES
THAT MONEY IS GOING TO GET
REDEPLOYED, AND THUS YOU'LL HAVE
A MARKET MELT-UP
YOU BUY THAT
>> I THINK IT'S POSSIBLE, SCOTT.
I REALLY DO.
I THINK THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE
ON WALL STREET THAT THINK THE
MARKET WILL GO HIGHER THE REST
OF THIS YEAR, BUT THERE'S VERY
FEW THAT THINK IT WOULD GO A LOT
HIGHER
MAYBE THE SURPRISE IS NOW THAT
IT'S GOING TO FALL OR GO HIGHER,
MAYBE IT BLOWS MUCH HIGHER THAN
IT SHOULD.
THEY COMPRISE NOW ABOUT 35% OF
MARKET CAPITALIZATION DOWN FROM
ALMOST 44% FROM EARLIER IN THE
RECOVERY, AND ALMOST 15
PERFECT -- IN OTHER WORDS,
CYCLICALITY IS VERY SCAROUS
RIGHT NOW.
SO TO DAVID ACE POINT, MAKE WHAT
YOU COULD DO IS TAKE --
INCLUDING NATIONAL MARKETS, AND
IF WE DO HIT A PERIOD OF
EXUBERANCE, THERE WOULD BE A LOT
OF UNDERWEIGHTED PORTFOLIOS THAT
NEED TO REDUCE THAT YOU ARE
UNDERWEIGHTS.
>>> GENTLEMAN, WE'RE GOING TO
LEAVE IT THERE
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US
HAVE A NICE WEEKEND.
>>> NEW HEADLINES CROSSING ON
THE ECONOMIC IMPACT OF THE NAFTA
UPDATE NEGOTIATED BY THE RHO
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION, NOT PASSED
YET, OF COURSE.
>> SCOTT, THE WHITE HOUSE HAS
CALLED THIS A TOP PRIORITY
THE U.S. TRADE REPRESENTATIVE IS
BREAKING WHAT IT EXPECTS TO BE
THE IMPACT ON ONE INDUSTRY, THE
AUTO INDUSTRY.
BASED ON CONVERSATIONS WITH AUTO
EXECUTIVES USTR SAYS THE NEW
DEAL WOULD RESULT IN SIGNIFICANT
INCREASES IN HIRING, AND OUTPUT
TO NEW INVESTMENT IN THE U.S.,
$23 BILLION IN NEW PURCHASING OF
PARTS, AND 76,000 NEW U.S. JOBS.
COMPANIES ARE EXPECTING ABOUT A
THIRD OF THOSE WILL BE ON THE
ASSEMBLY LINE AND THE REST FROM
VARIOUS SUPPLIERS, BUT IT COMES
IN ADVANCE OF A FULL INDEPENDENT
REPORT ON THE DEAL'S ECONOMIC
IMPACT
THAT'S EXPECTED TO BE RELEASED
A SENIOR USTR OFFICIAL SAYS THE
OFFICE DOES NOT KNOW WHAT THE
TRADE FINDINGS WILL BE, AND
THERE WAS NO MENTION IN A
BRIEFING OF THE POTENTIAL IMPACT
ON AUTO TARIFFS.
GUYS
>> KAYLA, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> WHETHER WE RETURN, IF YOU
THOUGHT THE RELEASE OF THE
MUELLER REPORT WAS THE END OF
THE FIGHT OVER THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S INVESTIGATION, DO NOT
HOLD YOUR BREATH
WE WILL TELL YOU WHAT COULD BE
NEXT, WHAT OTHER INVESTIGATIONS
COULD BE IN THE PIPELINE AND
WHAT IT MEANS FOR THE
PRESIDENT'S AGENDA.
>>> PLUS TWO MAJOR TECH IPOs HIT
THE TICKER TODAY
THEY ARE BOTH UP
WOULDN'T YOU LIKE TO HAVE SOME
ZOOM
WE'LL TELL YOU HOW THEY'RE
TRADING AND WHAT THAT MEANS FOR
THE WAVE OF OTHER STARTUPS
STAY WITH "POWER LUNCH."
When you rent from National...
it's kind of like playing your
own version of best ball.
Because here, you can choose any
car in the aisle,
even if it's a better car class
than the one you reserved.
So no matter what,
you're guaranteed to have a
perfect drive.
[LAUGHTER]
(VO) Go National. Go Like a Pro.
See what I did there?
>>> WELCOME BACK TO"POWER
LUNCH.
THE MUELLER REPORT IS OUT, BUT
IS IT OVER AND DONE WITH
I THINK WE ALL KNOW THE ANSWER
TO THAT.
WHERE DO WASHINGTON AND WALL
STREET GO FROM HERE?
LET'S BRING IN FORMER FEDERAL
PROSECUTOR, NOW A PARTNER AT
DICKINSON WRIGHT, JAMES FRANKEL,
AND BEN WHITE, AND TONY FRATTO,
FOUNDER, ALSO A CNBC
CONTRIBUTOR.
GENTLEMEN, WELCOME
WE ARE A BUSINESS NETWORK.
I'M GOING TO TRY TO MAKE IT A
BUSINESS AND POLITICAL AGENDA
DISCUSSION
I DON'T THINK WE'LL GET TO THE
BOTTOM OF WHAT IS IN THIS
INCREDIBLE REPORT.
IT'S A RICH READ
BUT LET ME START WITH YOU,
JACOB.
THE KEY TO THIS REPORT IS IN THE
BACK HALF, VOLUME 2, WHERE THE
DISCUSSION OF OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE BECOMES VERY DENSE
WOULD YOU, AS A PROSECUTOR,
HAVING SATISFIED IF YOU WERE NOT
ABLE TO INTERVIEW THE FOCUS OF
THAT OBSTRUCTION INQUIRY, YOU
WERE ONLY ALLOWED TO SUPPLY
WRITTEN QUESTIONS, AND YOU WERE
NOT ALLOWED AS PART OF YOUR
INQUIRY TO INCLUDE IN THOSE
QUESTIONS ANYTHING HAVING TO DO
WITH OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE?
>> I WOULD HAVE FOUND SUCH
LIMITATION RATHER OBJECTIONABLE,
NO QUESTION ABOUT THAT, BUT
ULTIMATELY WE HAVE TO LOOK AT
THE UNIQUE NATURE OF THIS
PROCESS ALL TOGETHER
THERE IS A CLEARLY, AS WE KNOW,
YOU KNOW, A ACCOMPLICE CAL
OVERTONE TO EVERYTHING THAT'S
DONE
ULTIMATELY THERE'S ONLY SO MUCH
THAT THE SPECIAL ARE SPECIAL
COUNSEL CAN DO, PARTICULARLY IF
HE'S TRYING TO GET OUT A FINAL
REPORT
HE DID THE RIGHT THING AND
FOLLOWED A TRADITIONAL MODEL,
WHICH IS GET ALL THE INFORMATION
ON PAPER, GET IT BEFORE THE
POLITICAL BODY, LET CONGRESS
MAKE THE DISCUSSION.
ULTIMATELY WHAT I HAVE READ INTO
THIS IS WHERE BOB MUELLER WAS
NOT PREPARED OR NOT ABLE TO MAKE
THE PROSECUTORIAL DECISION,
THERE'S STILL THAT LAT OF
CLARITY INTO THE INTERPRETATION
OF THE PHRASE HIGH CRIMES AND
MISDEMEANORS, BASICALLY PUNTING
TO CONGRESS TO MAKE THE
POLITICAL DECISION HOW TO GO
FORWARD.
>> THAT'S WHERE I THINK A LOT OF
US FEEL IT GOES ULTIMATELY, IS
THAT IT WAS A PUNT TO CONGRESS
I THINK ALSO MR. MUELLER FELT
THAT HIS HANDS WERE TIED, FAR
MORE THAN WE WERE LED TO
BELIEVE, BY A DEPARTMENT OF
JUSTICE RULING, INDICATING THAT
A SITTING PRESIDENT CANNOT BE
TRIED.
BEN, IS THE TRUMP AGENDA
BASICALLY NOW DEAD IN THE WATER?
BECAUSE I -- I FRANKLY CAN'T
IMAGINE THE DEMOCRATS ARE GOING
TO LET HIM GET MUCH DONE.
>> NO, THEY'RE NOT
I DON'T THINK IT'S DEAD IN THE
WATER.
A LOT OF HIS AGENDA IS TRADE
RELATED AND U.N. LAT RAY
UNILATERAL
IS.
>>> WHAT MUELLER HAS DONE IS
HANDED A BUNCH OF INFORMATION TO
CONGRESS
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO WORK WITH
TRUMP ON SIGNIFICANT
LEGISLATION.
>> TONY, IS THERE A CHANCE THAT
THE PRESIDENT LOSES ANY SUPPORT
AMONG HIS REPUBLICAN -- MAYBE
NOT THE BATES AND THE HARD-CORE
CONSTITUENTS, BUT OTHERS ON
CAPITOL HILL WHO MAY LOOK AT
THIS REPORT AND SEE THINGS THAT
ARE DAMNING WITHIN IT?
>> IT IS AN UGLY REPORT.
IF IT AT ALL TIMES SHORT OF ANY
CRIMINAL ACTIVITY, AND THAT'S AT
LEAST WHAT THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
DETERMINATION THAT HE COULD
MAKE, THERE'S A LOT OF THINGS IN
THERE THAT ARE PROPERTY PRETTY
TO READ AND ARE PRETTY DAMNING
FOR THE WHITE HOUSE AND
ACTIVITIES OF THE PRESIDENT
HIMSELF.
DOES THAT MOVE REPUBLICANS,
EITHER THE BASE OR MEMBERS
YOW KNOW THAT THERE'S ANYTHING
NEW IN HERE THAT COULD IMPACT
WHICH WAY THEY'RE GOING TO GO?
TRUMP IS INCREDIBLY POPULAR IN
THE REPUBLICAN PARTY
WE DIDN'T SEE HIM INCREASE HIS
POPULARITY WHEN THE BARR SUMMARY
CAME OUT
I DON'T THINK WE'LL SEE HIM
DECREASE HI POPULARITY WITH THIS
REPORT.
>> HAS THE BARB LOWERED?
YOU SAID EARLIER BARR DID THE
KIND OF JOB A REALLY GOOD
SPOKESMAN FOR THE PRESIDENT
WOULD DO
HOW DOES HE --
>> IT WAS UNUSUAL, AS A FORMER
SPOKESMAN FOR THE WHITE HOUSE,
WITH THE WHITE HOUSE SPEAKING
FOR PRESIDENTS, IT'S A KIND OF
JUMP YOU MIGHT EXPECT A GOOD
PRESS SECRETARY TO GIVE A
CLEANER PRESENTATION, AND I
DON'T THINK HE DID HIMSELF
FAVORS, BUT HE DID DO A FAVOR
FOR THE GUY IN THE ROUND OFFICE
WATCHING IT AND I THINK PAYING
CLOSE ATTENTION.
>> JACOB, WE SPOKE ABOUT THIS
WITH BEN, BUT WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT HOW THIS IMPACTS THE TRUMP
AGENDA, NOW THAT THAT IS AT
LEAST OUT THERE, IT'S NOT OVER
WITH, WE HAVE ESTABLISHED, BUT
AT LEAST OUT THERE
WHAT DOES IT MEAN FOR THE TRUMP
AGENDA ECONOMICALLY?
>> I THINK BACK TO, YOU KNOW, TO
A CONVERSATION BACK IN JUNE OF
217, WHEN WE WERE WATCHING THE
SENATE HEARINGS, THE MARKET WAS
HITTING ALL-TIME HIGHING DURING
THAT HEARINGS AT THE SENATE.
I THINK THERE'S ALWAYS A
RECOGNITION THAT ONCE THE BAD
INFORMATION HITS THE MARKET, IT
THEN ACTUALLY GETS ASSIMILATED
INTO THE MARKET, AND ULTIMATELY
THEN, THE AGENDA WILL PUSH
FORWARD HOWEVER THE ECONOMIC
WILL ALLOW IT TO DO SO, TO ALL
THE POINTS WE'VE GOT DISCUSSION
HERE
THE FACT THAT THERE REALLY IS
LITTLE NEW INFORMATION, YOU
KNOW, THAT'S COME OUT, THOUGH
IT'S A VERY UGLY REPORT FOR THE
PRESIDENT.
THE FACT REMAINS THE MARKETS ARE
GOING TO HAVE THE ABILITY TO
RESPOND.
BEN MAID THE POINT ABOUT THE
UNILATERAL NATURE OF THE TRADE
AGENDA
I DON'T THINK MUCH WILL CHANGE
IN THE MARKET, EVEN IF CONGRESS
WERE TO CONSIDER IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDINGS.
>> YEAH, I THINK THE POINT ON
THAT IS EVEN IF THE HOUSE WERE
TO GET TO IMPEACHMENT
PROCEDURES, NO -- THERE'S NOT
ENOUGH IN HERE TO CHANGE
REPUBLICANS' MINDS IN THE
SENATE, HE WOULD NOT EXONERATED
IN THE SENATE LIKE BILL CLINTON
WAS IN 1998.
>> THANK YOU, GUISE.
>>> MASTER CHEF ON BOBBY FLAY
MEETS NOAH AND MR. WONDERFUL AND
TIM SEYMOUR WILL SQUARE OFF.
ANOTHER DOWN DAY FOR THE SECTOR,
FALLING FOR THE THIRD STRAIGHT
DAY.
IS THAT SECTOR READY TO PERK UP
YTSOON
WE'LL DEBATE, COMING UP.
STAY WITH POWER.
What do advisors look for
in an ETF?
I tell clients, ETFs can
follow an index,
but which ones
target your goals?
It's not about quantity.
It's about quality.
No trendy stuff.
I want ETFs backed by research.
Is it built for the long-term?
My reputation depends on it.
FlexShares ETFs
are designed and managed around
investor objectives.
So you can advise
with confidence.
Before investing, consider the
fund's investment objectives,
risks, charges and expenses.
Go to flexshares.com
for a prospectus
containing this information.
Read it carefully.
When you look at the critical
issues facing our world,
what do you see?
We see a billion more
people breathing free.
We see access to fresh food
being the global norm,
not the exception.
We see homes staying cooler,
without the planet
getting warmer.
At Emerson,
when issues become inspiration,
focusing core strengths
to create a better world
isn't just a result,
it's a responsibility.
Emerson.
Consider It Solved.
Internet that puts
you in charge.
Alright boys, time to eat.
That handles anything.
[ crowd cheering ]
That protects
what's important.
And reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "POWER
LUNCH.
I'M MIKE SANTOLI
HEALTH CARE GETTING A SCARE,
DOWN 5% SINCE MONDAY, TURNS THE
ETF ANY NIVAR FOR THE YEAR
CRAIG JANSEN OF PIPER JAFFRAY A.
AND MIKE TEPPER ARE YOUR TRADING
TEAM TODAY
CRAIG, THIS HAS BEEN A SECTOR
THAT'S GONE FROM FIRSTO TO
WORST.
OBVIOUSLY FALLING APART.
IS THIS A LONGER LASTING,
STRUCTURAL CHANGE FOR THIS
GROUP?
>> MIKE, NO QUESTION THE HEALTH
CARE SECTOR HAS CAUGHT A COLD.
THE RELATIVE PERFORMANCE VERSUS
THE S&P HAS BEEN VERY PAINFUL
THE LAST 30 DAYS
WHEN HE BREAK DOWN THE CHART
HERE, YOU CAN SEE AN UPTREND
VIOLATION, THE DIVERGENCE, IT
LOOKS LIKE THE NEXT SUPPORT
COMES IN AT 85
WE'RE NOT BUYING AT THIS POINT
IN TIME.
WE'RE GOING TO WAIT FOR THE
SHAKEOUT
WHERE DOES THAT LEAVE YOU?
>> QUITE FRANKLY, THIS IS ALL
POLITICAL, 100% A RESPONSE TO
THE POSSIBILITY OF MEDICARE FOR
ALL BECOMING A REALITY, WHICH
WOULD CRUSH THE SECTOR
BERNIE SANDER IS GAINING TEAM,
GOING FROM A 12% TO 25% CHANCE
OF SECURING THE DEMOCRATIC
NOMINATION, AND THESE STOCKS
HAVE FELT THE BURN
WHETHER HE SECURES IT OR NOT, I
DON'T THINK MEDICARE FOR ALL
HAPPENS, SO I THINK THERE'S A
HUGE OPPORTUNITY
IN THE SHORT RUN I THINK THERE'S
POLITICAL HEADWINDS, BUT AS A
LONG-TERM INVESTOR I THINK YOU
HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY TO GET IN AS
A GOOD PRICE POUT.
COURTNEY, I WILL HAND IT BACK TO
YOU.
>>> THANK YOU, AHEAD ON "POWER
LUNCH", IPO WATCH, ZOOM AND
PINTEREST SCORING TODAY.
THE KEY DETAILS YOU NEED TO
KNOW, PLUS THE $3 MILLION HYPER
CAR THAT SOLD OUT IN JUST FIVE
DAYS
WE'RE JUST A WEEK AWAY FROM THE
2019 STOCK DRAFT
IT HAS ALREADY BEGUN, OR SHALL
WE SAY WHINING
MR. WONDERFUL JOINS US, WITH THE
LIST OF MANY GRIEVANCES.
"POWER LUNCH" WILL BE RIGHT
BACK
>> Announcer: NOW THE LATEST
FROM TRADING NATION AND A WORD
FROM OUR SPONSOR
WHEN THE ECONOMY IS EXPANDING,
INDUSTRIAL AND TECHNOLOGY STOCKS
HAVE HISTORICALLY OUTPERFORMED
THE BROADER MARKET
HOWEVER WHEN THE ECONOMY IS
CONTRACTING, MORE DEFENSIVE
SECTORS SUCH AS UTILITIES AND
STAPLES, TEND TO OUTPERFORM.
Does your Wealth Manager
measure up?
A CFA Charterholder does.
You've worked hard
to grow your wealth.
Make sure you're working
with a Wealth Manager
who can grow with you.
CFA Charterholders have
the investment expertise
to unlock opportunities other
advisors might not see.
Learn what a CFA Charterholdr
can do for you
at therightquestion.org
>>> I'M CONTESSA BREWER, HERE IS
YOUR UPDATE THIS HOUR.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ANNOUNCED HE'S
HAVING A GOOD DAY.
WHILE HE ATTENDED A WOUNDED
WARRIOR EVENT AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
THIS AS THE MUELLER REPORT WAS
BEING RELEASED.
>> I'M HAVING A GOOD DAY, TOO.
IT WAS CALLED NO COLLUSION, NO
OBSTRUCTION.
IT SHOULD NEVER HAPPEN TO
ANOTHER PRESIDENT AGAIN.
>>> NEW YORK POLICE SAY THEY
HAVE FORMALLY CHARGED MARK
LAMPRELIO WITH TRESPASSING
HE BROUGHT TWO GAS CANS OF GAS,
LIGHTER FLUID TO ST. PATRICK'S
CATHEDRAL.
>>> JAMES HOLZHAUER, HIS
STRATEGY STARTS AT THE BOTTOM OF
THE BOARD, HE ACCRUES LOTS OF
MONEY AND THEN BETS HUGE
AMOUNTS, OFTEN SAYING ALL IN,
AND JUST RAKES IN THE DOUGH.
I'M GOING TO TRY TO FIGURE OUT A
WAY -- HE'S A PROFESSIONAL
GAMBLER, SCOTT, SO I'M GOING TO
FIND ON WAY TO APPLY IT.
>> THEY CALL THAT STRTEJERY, I
THOUGHT.
PINTEREST RISING 28% RIGHT NOW
TAKE A LOOK AT ZOOM.
HIGHER BY -- ABOUT $63 A SHARE,
THAT'S UP 75% FROM ITS INITIAL
PRICING, WITH US NOW IS LESLIE
PICKER
GOOD TO HAVE YOU ALL HERE.
LESLIE, THE PRICE IS RIGHT, IT
APPEARS, FOR BOTH OF THESE.
>> PRICE IS RIGHT FOR NVESTORS
THAT'S CERTAINLY TRUE.
THE PRICE MAY BE LESS RIGHT FOR
THE COMPANIES RAISING MONEY,
GIVEN TODAY'S AFTER-MARK
PERFORMANCE.
I GUESS IF YOU'RE AN INVESTOR
THAT'S PUTTING YOUR MONEY INTO
THESE COMPANIES, LOOKING TO DO
FUTURE IPOs, THIS IS THE
AFTER-MARKET PERFORMANCE YOU
WANT TO SEE, BUT IF YOU'RE A
COMPANY THAT NEEDED THAT CAPITAL
TO GROW FURTHER IN THE FUTURE,
YOU MAY HAVE LIKED A BIT MORE
CASH IN THE COFFER.
>> NO DOUBT ABOUT THAT
DEE, PIN TRESEMME BE THE MORE
HOUSEHOLD NAME, IF YOU WILL, BUT
ZOOM, BOY, WHAT A GREAT DAY FOR
THOSE SHARES, UP 75%, AS WE
SAID, FOR A COMPANY THAT
ACTUALLY IS PROFITABLE
>> YEAH, SCOTT, THAT'S A VERY
GOOD POINT
I NOTICE PEN TRES DOESN'T WANT
TO BE CALLED A SOCIAL NETWORK,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT'S NOT?
CLOUD ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE.
IT'S REMARKABLE WHAT IT'S DONE
IN THIS VERY CROWDED FIELD
THIS IS A RARE BREED OF UNICORN.
NOT ONLY IS IT GROWING FASTER
THAN PINTEREST, UBER AND LYFT,
BUT AS YOU WANT, IT'S
PROFITABLE
NEARLY $8 MILLION OF PROFIT ON
ABOUT 350 MILLION OF REVENUE,
WHICH IS ACTUALLY HALF THAT OF
PINTEREST LAST YEAR, YET LOOK AT
THE VALUATIONS HERE.
TODAY'S PRICE ACTION PUTS ZOOM
AT ABOUT 16 BILLION MARKET CAP
THAT'S EVEN HIGHER THAN
PINTEREST.
>> YOU KNOW, JULIA, WHEN YOU
LOOK AT WHAT'S HAPPENED WITH
ZOOM, YOU CAN SAY, AS LESLIE
DID, THAT MAYBE SOME MONEY WAS
LEFT ON THE TABLE, BUT CERTAINLY
THE PEOPLE WHO OWN THAT STOCK
HAVE TO FEEL PRETTY GOOD,
BECAUSE THE STOCK IS NOW 76%
HIGHER THAN IT WAS JUST FIVE
HOURS AGO.
>>
AND WHO KNOWS WHERE IT'S GOING
TO BE IN SIX MONTHS.
>> YES
THERE ARE ABSOLUTELY LOCK-UP
PROVISIONS, TYLER.
IT'S WORTH NOTING THERE WAS THIS
DEBATE ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT IT
WOULD END UP BEING WORTH IN THE
PUBLIC MARKETS MORE OR LESS THAN
THE MOST RECENT PRIVATE MARKET
VALUATION.
THE START OF TRADING WAS CLEAR
THAT INVESTORS DO SEE IT BEING
WORTH MORE THAN THE LAST PRIVATE
MARKET VALUATION, THERE IS A
SENSE OF THE VALUE IN GOING
PUBLIC THERE
SO WE'LL SEE HOW THAT IMPACTS
THE VALUATION OF IPOs GOING
FORWARD.
IT'S GROWING THE REVENUE
SIGNIFICANTLY, AND MAKING IT'S
PROFITS SMALLER EVERY QUARTER
ONE OF THOSE IS INTERNAL NARD PA
EXPANSE.
WE'RE SEEING THE POTENTIAL TO
MAKE IT EASIER TO BUY THINGS TO
CONNECT CONSUMERS WITH THE
PERFORM OF THE
INDEPENDENCE-TO-END SHOPPING
EXPERIENCE
IT'S WORTH NOTING THAT PINTEREST
DOES NOT TAKE A CUT OF THE
E-COMMERCE THAT GOES THROUGH THE
PLATFORM, BUT IT WANTS
E-COMMERCE TO BE SUCCESSFUL.
>> I GREAT, JULIA, THAT IS AN
INTERESTING THING WE NEED TO
WATCH, HOW RETAILERS BEGINNING
TO EMBRACE IT.
WE HAVE TO LEAVE IT HERE TODAY,
LADIES
THANK YOU BOTH FOR JOINING US.
>>> OVER TO THE BOND MARKET.
RICK SANTELLI TRACKING THE
ACTION AT THE CME.
>> HI, WHAT A WILD DAY AND IF
YOU LOOK AT A MONTH TO DATE OF
TEN-YEAR YIELDS, WE CERTAINLY
HAVE COVERED A LOT OF GROUND.
YOU HAVE TO APPRECIATE THAT IT
JUST CLEARED THE ZONE WE'RE
ABOUT A QUARTER OF A PERCENT
AWAY
ONCE YOU TAKE THAT OUT TYLER,
BACK TO YOU.
>> MR. SANTELLI, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH
>>> THERE'S A SHINY NEW
AUTOMOBILE ON DISPLAY.
ROBERT FRANK AND A SPECIAL GUEST
ARE AT THE SHOW TO SHOW YOU.
ROBERT
>> TILE HER, WE ARE THIS THE ONE
AND ONLY TRACY MORGAN TO TELL
YOU ABOUT THE FASTEST NEW CAR.
>> I CALL IT EYE CANDY
THIS IS MY CAR
TANG A LOOK.
Through the AT&T Network,
Edge-to-Edge Intelligence gives
you the power to see every
corner of your growing business.
From finding out what's selling
best...
To managing your fleet...
To collaborating remotely with
your teams.
Giving you a nice big edge over
your competition.
That's the power of Edge-to-Edge
Intelligence.
♪♪
Feel that?
That's the beat of
global markets,
the rhythm of the world.
But to us,
it's the pace of tomorrow.
With ingenuity,
technologies,
and markets expertise
we create the possible.
And when you do that,
you don't chase
the pace of tomorrow.
You set it.
NASDAQ. REWRITE TOMORROW.
[ telephone rings ]
[ Client ] - Hey Maya.
Hey! You still thinking
about opening your own shop?
Every day.
I think there are some ways
to help keep you on track.
And closer to home.
Edward Jones grew to a trillion
dollars in assets under care,
by thinking about your
goals as much as you do.
>>> YOU KNOW THERE'S EXCITEMENT
AROUND A NEW CAR WHEN IT SPORTS
A MULTIMILLION DOLLAR PRICE TAG,
BUT STILL SELLS OUT IN LESS THAN
A WEEK
ROBERT FRANK IS AT THE NEW YORK
AUTO SHOW WITH MORE.
>> Reporter: THIS IS THE FASTEST
PRODUCTION CAR IN EXISTENCE.
IT GOES 300 MILES AN HOUR, COSTS
$3 MILLION, THE BEST PART IS
THAT IT SOLD OUT IN JUST FIVE
DAYS
IT'S MADE BY KOENIGSEGG.
IF YOU DON'T KNOW THE NAME,
YOU'RE PROBABLY NOT ALONE.
IT'S ONE OF THE ULTRA--EXCLUSIVE
BRANDS IN THE CAR WORLD KNOWN
ONLY TO THE SUPER-RICH
MOST OF THE CUSTOMERS ARE YOUNG
ENTREPRENEURS, OBVIOUS IN TECH
THEY PROBABLY WON'T DRIVE IT 300
MILES AN HOUR, BUT THEY LIKE THE
STATUS OF KNOWING THAT THEY CAN.
>> KNOWING THAT YOUR CAR IS THE
FASTERS IN THE WORLD AND IF YOU
PUT IT IN THE HANDS OF A
PROFESSIONAL DRIVER ON A SAFE
PLACE, THAT IT CAN DO THAT, THAT
IT CAN BREAK THOSE RECORDS AND
MAKE HISTORY, THAT'S A COOL
THING.
>> Reporter: VERY COOL THING
THE OTHER COOL THINGS IS THE
NAME JESKO IS NAMED AFTER THE
FOUNDER'S FATHER WHO PUT HIS
ENTIRE SAVINGS, WHEN IT WAS
ABOUT TO GO UNDER.
HOPEFULLY HE CAN PAY HIS DAD
BACK.
>> ROBERT.
THANK YOU, SWEET RIDE.
EXPENSIVE RIDE.
>> BUT IF THE TRAFFIC IS STUFF
ON THE CROSS-BRONX, YOU'RE NOT
GOING FAST.
>> YOU'RE SITTING PRETTY, AREN'T
YOU?
>> YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD, STYLING.
>> SMOKIES WILL BE CHASING YOU
QUICK, NO MATTER WHERE YOU DRIVE
IT.
>>> THE DRAFT ORDER IS SET, THE
STOCK LIST IS FINALIZED.
WE ARE IN FINAL COUNTDOWN FOR
THE "POWER LUNCH" STOCK DRAFT.
STILL AHEAD.
TIM SEYMOUR HAS THE FIRST PICK
MR. O'LEARY HAS A LOT OF
COLATSMPIN APPARENTLY, NOT SO
WONDERFUL-FEELING TODAY.
WE'RE BACK IN TWO MINUTES.
We got no free pass.
Everything we have,
we've earned.
The unmistakable Lexus IS.
Lease the 2019 IS 300 for
$329 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
>>> A RAE PEAT WON'T COME EASY
FOR NICK VALERIE
WILL THE WALL STREET MENTALIST
TAME MR. WONDERFUL
AND CAN THE MAVENS DELIVER
IT'S A SUPER SIZED STOCK DRAFT
>>> WELL, YOU JUST HEARD IT
THERE.
WE'RE ONE WEEK AWAY FROM THE
BIGGEST STOCK DRAFT EVER
FORGET THE NFL
NOR GET ABOUT KYLER MURRAY,
OKAY, FOLKS.
THE DRAFT ORDER HAS BEEN SET
WE PICKED IT YESTERDAY
TIM SEYMOUR GETS THE NUMBER ONE
PICK
THINGS DID NOT TURN OUT SO WELL
FOR OUR FIRST -- OUR CHAMPION
BEFORE LAST, PICK NUMBER EIGHT
AS A MATTER OF FACT, KEVIN WAS
SO FURIOUS HE CALLED OUR
PRODUCER GENO LATE LAST NIGHT
AND LEFT A NOT-SAFE-FOR-WORK
MESSAGE VOICING HIS GRIEVANCES,
THREATENING LEGAL ACTION AGAINST
OUR DRAFT COMMISSIONERS.
HE EVEN TALKED ABOUT COLLUSION
KEVIN O'LEARY, TIM SEYMOUR,
WELCOME.
>> DISAPPOINTING.
>> YOU SUSPECT A DEEP STATE
CONSPIRACYIST HERE, KEVIN?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S THE
CHINESE OR THE RUSSIANS BUT
SOMETHING IS WRONG IN THE STATE
OF DENMARK HERE, AND I WILL TELL
YOU WHY.
YOU TALK ABOUT ANY LEG, YOU
REMEMBER I WON THIS THING TWO
DRAFTS AGO
I CRUSHED THE COMPETITION.
>> YESTERDAY'S NEWS.
KEEP GOING.
>> DOESN'T MATTER.
NOW THAT I CAME IN BELOW TIM
SEYMOUR, I SHOULD OBVIOUSLY IN
ANY LEAGUE GET THE FIRST PICK.
BUT THE COMMISSIONER SENT MY
THIS NOTICE LAST NIGHT, I CALLED
MUELLER'S OFFICE IMMEDIATELY
DEMANDING FULL TRANSPARENCY.
WE NEED AN INVESTIGATION
THERE'S COLLUSION.
THERE'S SOME KIND OF A PROBLEM
HERE AND WE HAVE TO AIR THIS
IT'S STRONG, ABSOLUTELY STRONG
I AM NOT THE KIND OF GUY WHO
LIKES TO BUT I'M READY TO
LITIGATE.
>> KEVIN, YOU FINISH ED FIFTH
LAST YEAR, NOT IN LAST PLACE.
>> OUT OF HOW MANY THOUGH?
>> OUT OF EIGHTH.
>> YOU MIGHT AS WELL HAVE BEEN
IN LAST.
>> IT FELT LIKE LAST TO MR.
WONDERFUL.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE TALKING,
TIM, YOU HAVE AN AFFINITY FOR
CANNABIS STOCKS.
>> I DO.
ALTHOUGH WE HAVE TO BE CAREFUL
ABOUT THE INFLUENCE WE'RE UNDER
FOR THIS DRAFT
IN FACT, I THINK BASED UPON THE
MOVE AND THE HIGHS THESE STOCKS
ARE ON, THAT MAY NOT BE MY
STRATEGY IN 2019, TYLER.
>> WE HAVE A LIST OF 60 STOCKS
INCLUDING TILRAY, CANNABIS
COMPANY.
YOU CAN BUY BITCOIN IF YOU WANT
OR OIL
KEVIN, IT SAYS IN MY NOTES YOU
AND FELL KBROETER BETHENNY
FRANKEL MAY TEAM UP SOMEHOW AND
COLLUDE?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT WILL
HAPPEN
IT WILL BE A NASTY SMACKDOWN
NEXT THURSDAY WHEN IT HAPPENS.
I HAVE NOT DECIDED MY STRATEGY
YET BUT I KNOW THERE'S SOMETHING
WRONG HERE
I WANT TO TELL YOU SOMETHING
ELSE I HAVE A BIG BEEF WITH, I'M
A DIVIDEND INVESTOR.
I'M ABOUT RETURN OF CAPITAL.
I DON'T GET MY DIVIDENDS
INCLUDED
I WANT TO SHORT TILRAY, I KCAN'
DO THAT!
I WANT THE CHAIRMAN TO LISTEN TO
MY GRIEVANCES OR MUELLER'S GOING
TO BE ALL OVER THEM
>> IF IT'S SNOWY, WINDY, RAINING
DAY IN THE MEADOWLANDS, YOU HAVE
TO PLAY IN THE CONDITIONS OUT
THERE.
I WOULD STOP WHINING AND BRING
YOUR A-GAME.
TEAMING UP WITH THE OTHER TEAM
SOUNDS LIKE A SIGN OF WEAKNESS
BOTTOM LINE IS THIS IS A UNIQUE
SET OF CONDITIONS FOR THE STOCK
DRAFT.
IT'S A LIMITED HORIZON
IF ANYTHING, IT'S AN OPTION AND
NOT WORRYABOUT DIVIDENDS.
>> TIM, YOU GET THREE PICKS.
YOU HAVE TO HOLD THESE FROM
APRIL 25th UNTIL JANUARY 31.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO
BE AVAILABLE WHEN IT COMES UP
IS, LIKE ANOTHER DRAFT
CAN YOU GIVE US ANY INSIGHT INTO
WHAT STOCKS YOU WILL PICK
WITHOUT GIVING TOO MUCH AWAY
YOU DON'T KNOW IF THEY WILL BE
AVAILABLE WHEN IT'S YOUR TURNS
ANYWAY
>> MUM'S THE WORD, BUT I DO HAVE
NUMBER ONE PICK, THIS COULD BE
MY AUNDRAY BRUCE TIM COUCH
MOMENT
MAYBE I WILL TRADE BACK WITH
KEVEN ON THE NUMBER FIVE PICK.
WHO KNOWS?
BUT MY TACTIC IS FIND DEEP VALUE
OR NAMES THAT HAVE SOME KIND OF
DISLOCATION.
I WOULD LIKE AN EVENT-DRIVEN
STORY FOR A 12-MONTH DRAFT
ESPECIALLY SOMETHING I THINK HAS
BEEN TRADING OUT OF THE MONEY.
>> KEVIN, GIVEN YOUR LACK OF
SUCCESS -- SORRY -- WITH BLUE
APRON A YEAR AGO, WOULD YOU
STILL CONSIDER PICKING ONE OF
THE NEWER STAGE PUBLIC COMPANIES
LIKE A PINTEREST OR ZOOM OR
LYFT
>> FIRST OF ALL, I'M NOT TAKING
THE BLAME OF BLUE APRON.
I'M MANY BLAMING JIM CRAMER WHO
SAID --
>> DON'T THROW CRAMER UNDER THE
BUS!
>> CRAMER WIPED ME OUT
I'M GOING BACK TO MY ROOTS
MY BIGGEST CONCERN IS BEST PICKS
WILL BE AT THE BOTTOM OF THE
LIST, WE KNOW THAT'S AN OUTRAGE,
BUT I WILL FIGURE OUT HOW TO
CRAWL BACK FROM THE BASEMENT
HERE AND CRUSH SEYMOUR, CRUSH
HIM, FOR THIS IMPETULANCE.
THAT'S WHAT IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> I WILL TELL YOU, WE HAVE A
PERIOD FOR THE STOCK TO GO
THROUGH THE DISCUSSION OF THE
TRANSITION
WE KNOW IT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN
OVERNIGHT BUT I THINK THERE'S
BEEN A CASE YOU CAN SEE
SOMETHING IS HAPPENING.
>> BUT THAT'S THE TIME OF A
RERATING STORY THAT IS AT LEAST
OPPORTUNISTIC IN THIS
ENVIRONMENT.
>> EXACTLY.
>> YOU KNOW, SO MUCH OF THIS IS
ABOUT TIMING
BECAUSE TWO YEARS AGO WHEN,
KEVIN, YOU WON, ONE OF THE
STOCKS THAT WEIGHED DOWN
CHARLES' WAY WAS AMD
HE WAS IN LAST PLACE THAT YEAR
THE NEXT YEAR, THE THIRD PICK OF
NICK LOWERY'S CHOICES WAS AMD,
AND THAT WAS THE STOCK THAT MADE
HIM THE WINNER LAST YEAR
SO THE LAST SHALL BE FIRST
SOMETIMES.
>> LARRY PUT IT RIGHT THROUGH
THE UPRIGHTS ON THAT
I WILL SAY THE SAME THING THE
YEAR BEFORE, VALENT WAS THE
WORST STOCK IN THE MARKET FOR
THE PROCEEDING YEAR AND NUMBER
ONE PERFORMER FOR ME
I THINK YOU HAVE TO FIND
OPPORTUNITIES WHERE COMPANIES
ARE AT SOME INFLECTION POINT
EITHER IN THEIR REVENUE MODEL OR
BALANCE SHEET CLEANUP, THOSE ARE
THE THINGS THAT WILL MOVE THE
MOST.
>> KEVIN, LAST WORD TO YOU, YOU
MAKE YOUR COMMISSIONER TO THE
APPEAL HERE WITH
>> I'M GOING TO BRING MY BEST
GAME, OBVIOUSLY.
THIS HAS BECOME VERY IMPORTANT
TO ALL OF US
WHO KNEW THE LEAGUE WOULD BECOME
SO IMPORTANT
BUT I'M NOT PLANNING ON LOSING
EVER SIN SO YOU MIGHT AS WELL
JUST PERMANENTLY PRINT MY NAME
AND THAT TROPHY.
I'M COMING IN TO GET IT.
YOU WILL NOT EVEN TOUCH THAT,
SEYMOUR.
>> THIS IS VERY PERSONAL
VERY PERSONAL.
>> NEXT THURSDAY 2:00 ON "POWER
LUNCH," WE'RE GOING TO HAVE FUN
ALL YEAR WATCHING THE BIG
SMACKDOWN.
>> THANK YOU, GENTLEMEN.
>>> STICARNDOR "ECK OU FCHK,
PLEASE," NEXT ON "POWER LUNCH.
[Leaf Blower]
You should be mad
at leaf blowers.
[beep]
You should be mad your neighbor
always wants to hang out.
And you should be mad your
smart fridge
is unnecessarily complicated.
But you're not mad,
because you have E*TRADE
which isn't complicated.
Their tools make trading
quicker and simpler.
So you can take on the
markets with confidence.
Don't get mad.
Get E*TRADE and
start trading today.
Your brain is an amazing thing.
But as you get older,
it naturally begins to change,
causing a lack of sharpness,
or even trouble with recall.
Thankfully, the breakthrough in
Prevagen helps your brain
and actually improves memory.
The secret is an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
>> I WAS GOING TO DO THE IPOs.
>> WHY NOT
>> ZOOM AND PINTEREST BECAUSE
THEY'RE WILDLY SUCCESSFUL.
TODAY, THE QUESTION IS WILL THEY
CONTINUE TO BE
REMEMBER SOME OF THESE OTHER
HIGH-FLYING TECHNOLOGY IPOs,
MANY OF WHOM HAD NICE POPS, AND
THEN A MONTH LATER OR THREE
MONTHS LATER YOU TAKE A LOOKND