You got out right
at the right time.
You had the $50,000 case.
Open your case.
Wow, Missy Silverman
is the lucky one.
Ran inf here
with $165,000,
plus she's going on
a dream vacation
thanks to Princess Cruises.
We've got to go run ourselves.
I'm Howie Mandel.
I'll see you next time
right here
on "Deal or No Deal."
male announcer: It's a battle
of good and evil.
[exciting music]
announcer:
26 women on a mission...
[cheering]
announcer:
To help defeat the banker...
♪ ♪
announcer: In an epic place
where anything's possible.
♪ ♪
- Whoo.
announcer:
Tonight...
With $1 million on the line...
♪ ♪
There's no one more fearless
than Justin Uhart.
[cheers and applause]
- You've inspired everyone
in this room.
You saved the life of
a young lady.
- Whoo.
[cheers and applause]
announcer:
And the this hero's in it
for the long haul.
- Whoo.
And I have to have at least
six figures.
Do you hear that, banker?
No deal.
[cheering]
Playing with some fire
right now.
- I'm starting to feel
the flames.
announcer:
Will his heroics guide him
to the prize?
- Man, you are throwing me
through
a whirlwind of emotions
right now.
[cheers and applause]
[exciting music]
announcer:
From Universal Orlando Resort,
where unforgettable
experiences
and adventure come together...
♪ ♪
"Deal Or No Deal."
[cheers and applause]
- Welcome to "Deal Or No Deal."
I'm Howie Mandel,
and I just...
Can I just say something?
I love this show.
I really love the show.
[cheers and applause]
There's so much to love
about it.
I love watching people win
life-changing amounts of money.
I love this stage,
I love this crowd.
[cheers and applause]
But you know what I love
most of all?
These two words:
ladies, please.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
Hello, ladies.
all:
Hello, Howie.
- [chuckles]
Sometimes this show is
all about the money,
and sometimes it is all about
the player.
Now tonight it's about
this next player.
This is very special.
He is something special.
He really is, watch this tape.
- Many of you are waking up
to the unimaginable
this morning.
A mass shooting at
a country music concert
on the Las Vegas Strip
kills at least 50 people,
more than 200 others wounded.
- I just saw her on
the ground,
and, um, she was looking
for help.
And I--I don't know why,
I just--I stopped,
and I saw the wound
and I saw the blood
and I just--just stopped it
best I could.
- If it wasn't for him,
I would not be here.
- Please welcome
a real-life hero,
Justin Uhart.
[cheers and applause]
- [laughs]
[exciting music]
- Whoo.
What's up, Howie?
- Hey, man.
- How's it going, man?
- Wonderful.
- Whoo.
Yeah, let's go.
- That's all for you, buddy.
- Whoo.
- Thank you.
- That's all for you.
It's crazy.
[applause]
- You know, first of all,
that tape is incredibly moving,
and, you know,
we talk about heroic deeds,
but you actually lived it
and did it.
And that woman is alive
because of you.
Do you stay in contact
with her?
- Oh, yes.
- Have you seen her?
- Every day we keep in touch.
- Where is she?
- She's from Canada.
Actually, check this out.
- What are these?
- Boom.
- Canada.
That's the Canadian flag.
[applause]
I love that.
You just made me homesick.
[laughter]
- So, these are actually
from Jan.
She sent them from--
- The woman whose life
you saved.
- Yes, sent them.
These are my lucky charms.
I got lucky enough to save her,
and I can't wait to call her
and say "hi."
- She's in your socks.
- She got into the socks,
love the socks.
[laughs]
- So, you haven't had a chance
to see her--
- I have--I haven't seen her
since the hospital.
- But that is wonderful.
So, you are truly a hero--
- Thank you.
- You deserve...
- Thanks.
- A life-changing amount
of money.
Tell me more about yourself,
like what do you do?
I know you're a hero,
but what do you do...
- I grew up in
a really small town
called, Minden, Nevada.
With--we have a whole
six stoplights.
And now I'm in Vegas,
and I'm a loan officer.
I'm 26 and hoping to win
a whole bunch of money
and have fun with you guys.
[cheers and applause]
- That is so great.
Are you in a relationship?
Are you married?
- I'm not married;
I'm good right now.
So, hey, ladies.
[chuckles]
- [laughing]
[applause]
Ready to start now?
- I'm ready.
- Okay, let's do it.
- Let's play.
[cheers and applause]
- So, each of those ladies
is holding a case.
Each case has a different
amount of money in it,
from $1 million...
- Whoo.
[cheers and applause]
- All the way down to
the penny.
- All right.
- Now, we don't know what case
is holding what amount.
They were all packed randomly
by a third party.
We don't know where that
$1 million is.
Do you think you know?
- Oh, I got it.
I got my case picked out
right now.
- Go ahead, pick a case.
- Number 19.
- Okay.
Natasha.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
- Whoo.
Thanks.
- I'm from Vegas.
- Oh, okay.
- So, God bless you.
- Thank you,
nice to meet you.
- Oh, wow.
Is there a reason you chose 19?
[cheers and applause]
- Last three times I have been
to Chinese food
and gotten a fortune cookie...
- Right.
- This number has been on
all of them.
So, it's a sign.
It's gotta be a sign.
- Could be a sign.
- [laughs]
- So, let's find out
if your fortune cookies
were right by opening
those cases.
What's ever in those cases
is not in your case.
We will start by opening up
six cases.
- Number 16.
[cheers and applause]
- Jessica Lee, open your case.
♪ ♪
- 25...
- Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
- That's good, five more.
- Five more.
Number seven.
- Number seven.
- Lucky seven, lucky seven.
- Jordana.
Jordana, open your case.
♪ ♪
[audience groans]
- Three quarters of a million
dollars, but...
- Starting off heavy.
- I mean, that hurts,
but look at all the big amounts
still in play,
including 1 million--
- Right there.
Right there.
- Four more cases.
- [sighs] 17.
- 17, that's Ashley.
Open the case.
♪ ♪
- Yeah.
There we go.
- Three more.
[applause]
- 23.
- 23...Anne Julia,
open your case.
♪ ♪
- Yeah.
Whoo.
- Whoo.
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
- You're doing good.
You're doing good.
- Whoo.
- Three more cases.
- I'm feeling 11.
Let's go.
- Okay, that's Brittany.
Brittany, open your case.
♪ ♪
- Yes.
- There you go.
- Yes!
[whooping]
- And one more.
- Oh, my God.
Number 9.
- Number 9, that's Patricia.
Last one, open your case.
Left side.
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Yes.
- Five tiny amounts,
one big amount.
Everybody wants you to walk out
of here
with as much money as possible.
They want that to be
the $1 million case.
- It'll be it.
That's it.
- There is one person
in this room
that does not want that
for you,
and that is that lady up there.
She's about to call
with her offer to buy your case
and send you home right now.
♪ ♪
Hello.
Okay.
She says she truly respects
your heroism.
[cheers and applause]
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- But this is business.
So, your first offer...
Is $15,000.
[audience booing]
Listen, this is
"Deal Or No Deal" 2.0.
It's a little different than
the original "Deal Or No Deal."
There is one little twist
and that is
the contestant, you, have
the opportunity to negotiate.
- Ooh.
- Once in the game you could
present the banker
with a counteroffer.
You only can do that once,
and if she turns down
that offer,
you gotta play on.
So, I am going to ask you
right now...
- Ooh.
- Justin Uhart,
deal or no deal?
[audience exclaiming]
- Well...
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
15,000, that's a lot of money.
- Yeah.
- But it's so early
in the game,
so I'm gonna say it
right now...
No deal.
- No deal! Five cases to open!
We will continue with our hero
when we come back.
[exciting music]
SARAH'S LAST TUITION
PAYMENT, SENT OFF.
FEELING GOOD?
OH YEAH.
NOW I'M READY TO
FOCUS ON MY PROJECT.
♪ ♪ ♪
THIS IS WHY WE PLAN.
YOU NEVER CEASE
TO AMAZE ME, MAYA.
SEE HOW INVESTING WITH A J.P.
MORGAN ADVISOR CAN HELP YOU.
VISIT YOUR LOCAL CHASE BRANCH.
TO BE NOBODY BUT YOURSELF IN A
WORLD WHICH IS DOING IT'S BEST
TO MAKE YOU EVERYBODY ELSE...
♪ ♪ ♪
MEANS TO FIGHT
THE HARDEST BATTLE,
WHICH ANY HUMAN BEING
CAN FIGHT AND NEVER STOP.
DOES THIS SOUND DISMAL?
IT ISN'T.
♪ ♪ ♪
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL LIFE ON EARTH.
♪ ♪ ♪
(MEG VO)
I can just suck up my
endometriosis pain...
Or I can...
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL LIFE ON EARTH.
(DIANE VO)
I can keep apologizing...
Or I can...
(SHERRY VO)
I can hope my pain gets better
on its own...
Or I can talk to
my gynecologist today!
(AVO)
You didn't choose to have
endometriosis...
but you can choose to ask
if ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA is specifically
developed for women
with moderate to severe
endometriosis pain.
In clinical trials,
ORILISSA was proven to reduce 3
common types of
endometriosis pain,
painful periods,
pelvic pain in between
periods,
and pain with sex.
Don't use ORILISSA if you are or
may be pregnant,
have osteoporosis,
severe liver disease, or are
taking drugs like
cyclosporine or gemfibrozil.
It may cause abnormal
liver tests.
ORILISSA may change your
periods, making it hard
to know if you are pregnant.
It does not prevent pregnancy.
Use birth control that does not
contain hormones.
ORILISSA may cause suicidal
thoughts or actions.
It may also cause bone loss.
Ask your gynecologist if
ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA. Made for endo pain.
[exciting music]
[cheers and applause]
- Hey, welcome back to
"Deal Or No Deal."
I'm Howie Mandel
and this is Justin Uhart.
- Hey.
- This young man is
our Vegas hero.
I can't get over how heroic
you are
and how composed you are.
You said you chose this case,
you believe this is
the $1 million-dollar case
because of numbers you read
in fortune cookies.
- Fortune cookies, yeah, three.
- Three fortune cookies.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- All right.
You have five cases to open.
- All righty.
Number four.
- Number four.
Brenda, open your case.
- Nice and low.
We're gonna keep that going.
- Small amount, small amount.
That's okay.
No, that's good.
- That's good.
All right.
- I'll take that.
Four more.
- 18.
[cheers and applause]
- Elissa.
Elissa is also from Canada.
- Oh, all right.
- Elissa, open your case.
- Be lucky, Elissa, come on.
♪ ♪
- Ooh.
- 100,000, not terrible,
not terrible.
Three more cases.
- The big number's up there.
[cheers and applause]
- 22.
- Anchal, open your case.
♪ ♪
$1,000.
1,000.
That's really good,
two more cases.
- Two more low,
two more low.
13, get rid of it.
- Lucky 13,
that's Mahogany Lox.
Mahogany Lox, open your case.
- Penny, dollar, penny, dollar.
Nice and low.
Yes.
Yes!
Whoo!
- One more.
One more.
- 20.
[cheers and applause]
- It's Amanza.
This is the last one
before the next offer.
Keep it on the left side,
open your case.
- Here we go.
♪ ♪
- Ooh.
- Ooh, 200,000.
Okay, but you're good.
All that has to go away.
[phone ringing]
- Ooh.
[chuckles]
- You always get this nervous
when a lady calls?
- It depends if they're
that pretty.
[laughs]
- She might be very pretty.
Hello.
♪ ♪
She said she refuses to lose
to someone who is basing
their entire strategy
on fortune cookies.
[laughter]
[applause]
All right.
How old are you again?
- 26.
This is the beginning
of a career.
So, money now would mean
more...
- Setting up my future.
- It really is.
- I want a home.
- So, I'm gonna tell you
something...
The offer is $33,000.
Yeah.
- It went up.
- Right,
you said "buy a home,"
is that something you wanna do?
- I do.
- This could get you a home.
- It would be a down payment,
yeah.
- So, this is a big decision,
isn't it?
- It's getting more and more.
- Well, talk about
"more and more,"
it's not just you.
You have brought supporters
with you, too, haven't you?
- The best supporters.
- Well, let's meet them.
[cheers and applause]
- You are?
- Howdy.
- It's great to be here, man.
Glad to finally meet you.
- It's good to meet you.
Love your hair.
- Likewise, thank you.
So, I've known Justin
for the last two years,
but I feel like I've known
him my whole life.
As a Marine I was trained
to do the things that he did.
- Yeah.
- And he did 'em.
So, I'm just proud to call him
my friend
and, honestly, a brother.
- Whoo!
All right, all right.
- And you are?
- Hey, Howie, I'm Johnny.
- Hi, Johnny.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm Justin's middle school
buddy.
We've been best friends
for life.
He's always supported me
when I did my stint
in the military.
- Okay, great.
Hi, young lady.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- Good.
- Who are you?
- I'm Cassie.
I'm Justin's little sister.
He's my big brother, you know,
he's always been my hero,
and now he's a hero
to everybody else.
[cheers and applause]
- So, your friend
and your brother
has just been offered $33,000.
- Yeah.
- You can either take the deal,
or you can counter-offer.
I want you to talk
to your friends.
I'm gonna ask you,
Justin Uhart,
deal or no deal?
Talk to them.
- We both got the Vegas-side
opinion here:
you just keep going.
- Yes.
- Just keep going?
- We're going all the way,
baby.
- Just rally it up?
- You got plenty of numbers,
keep going.
- Let it ride?
- Let it ride.
- No deal.
Four cases to open.
- Whoo-whoo.
[cheers and applause]
- So, everybody here considers
you a hero.
I've never got to ask you,
do you have any heroes?
- Yeah, absolutely.
My childhood hero was, uh,
Emmitt Smith.
I'm a big Dallas Cowboy fan.
So...he's a standup guy,
and he's an amazing athlete,
hall of famer.
And he--I would love to meet
him someday,
but yeah, he's someone
I've always looked up to.
- All right.
It's neat to hear a hero
who has a hero.
Four cases.
- All right, four cases,
Justin, here you go.
- 15.
- Whoo.
- 15, that's Maddi.
I think you NFL in your family.
- I do, unfortunately not
the Cowboys, but...
- Oh.
- [chuckles]
- they still have a place
in my heart.
- Open your case.
- Low, low.
- Penny.
♪ ♪
- Yes!
[cheers and applause]
- Good job, good job!
- Three more.
- Eight.
- Here we go.
- That's Neka.
Neka, open your case.
- Left side, left side.
- Low, low.
- Left side.
- Low.
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah.
- All right,
let's keep it going.
12.
- Whoo.
- Good number, good number.
- Sarati, open the case.
- Give me that dollar.
Where's that dollar?
- Does she have the dollar?
5 grand, that's good.
- I'll take it.
- That's good.
- One more case.
- All right, Justin, on more.
- Yeah, boy!
- Here we go, here we go.
- Number one.
- One.
- Nice, nice.
- Soraya, you think you got
a small amount in there?
- That's the goal.
- [laughs]
Okay.
Open your case.
♪ ♪
- Whoo.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my God!
- Take a run.
[cheers and applause]
That was a great round.
- Oh, let's go up.
Let's go up, banker.
Let's go up.
- That was a great round.
A huge offer when you return.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Whoo.
- Yeah!
announcer: Justin's feeling
like a million bucks.
- You believe the million
dollars is in your case.
The million dollars is still
on the board.
announcer: But to ensure
he stays on top...
- Have to have at least
six figures before I'm out.
No deal!
- Oh, my God.
announcer: He'll have
to bring in
some extra offense.
- I want you to meet your hero.
- Oh!
- Emmitt Smith!
♪ ♪
[farmers bell]
(Driver)
Relax, it's just a bug.
That's not a bug,
that's not a bug!
(Burke)
Hit and Drone.
Seen it, covered it.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
Really?
[horn honks]
Man this is what I feel like
when I wear regular shoes,
cramped and uncomfortable.
We can arrange a little upgrade.
Which is why I wear Skechers...
Wide Fit shoes.
They have extra room throughout.
They're like a luxury
ride for my feet.
Try Skechers
Wide Fit shoes.
Allergies with sinus
congestion and pressure?
You won't find relief here.
They're like a luxury
ride for my feet.
Go to the pharmacy counter
for powerful Claritin-D.
While the leading allergy spray
only relieves 6 symptoms,
Claritin-D relieves 8, including
sinus congestion and pressure.
Claritin-D relieves more.
Gary, Gary, Gary...
I am PROUD of you, my man.
Making simple, smart cash back
choices...
With Quicksilver from
Capital One.
You're earning UNLIMITED 1.5%
cash back
on EVERY purchase, EVERYWHERE.
Like on that new laptop.
Quicksilver keeps things simple,
Gary.
And smart, like you!
And I like that.
I guess I am pretty smart.
Don't let that go to your head,
Gary.
What's in your wallet?
From the start, the C-Class
was ahead of its time.
Still, we never stopped
making it stronger.
Faster.
Smarter.
Because to be the best,
is to never ever stop
making it better.
There's never been
a better time
to become part of the
Mercedes-Benz family.
Visit the Mercedes-Benz
Spring Event
before April 30th
for exceptional lease
and financing offers
on the 2019 C 300.
[exiting music]
- Hey, welcome back
to "Deal Or No Deal."
I'm Howie Mandel,
and this is Justin Uhart.
- Hey.
- This young man is
our Vegas hero.
Got a lot of nervous energy,
don't ya?
- Howie, I'm getting nervous.
I gotta run.
I'm feeling it.
- You gotta run?
- I gotta do a lap.
- Are you gonna be back--
You wanna lap?
- A lap, like a victory lap.
- Go ahead.
- I gotta do a victory lap.
Victory lap, victory lap,
victory lap, victory lap.
[cheers and applause]
- [chuckles]
Okay.
- [laughs]
- I feel loose.
- I had no idea what you were
saying.
I thought you were saying
good-bye.
"I know I'm nervous,
but I gotta run.
Sorry,
can't finish the game."
- Not that time.
- You should stay right till
the end of the game,
because it gets so exciting.
I'm telling you.
[laughter]
You ready for an offer?
- I am; let's go, banker.
Come on, give me
something good.
[phone ringing]
- Hello.
- Ooh-ooh.
- That million's in your case.
You're standing next to it.
- Okay.
Okay, got it.
[applause]
Wow, you did well.
- Ooh.
She's not too happy with me,
huh?
- She's not too happy.
- [laughs]
- The more unhappy she gets,
the better the offers get.
- Then we get happy.
Yeah, so...
Are--are you gonna tell me?
- Yeah.
[laughter]
- Lay it on us, Howie;
let's hear it.
- I know, it just--you know,
anticipation is fun, isn't it?
- Howie.
- It was.
[laughter]
- Want me to make it fun again?
- Make really fun,
give me good news.
- More than double: $76,000.
[cheers and applause]
That's a lot of money.
- That's the most money
I've ever had a chance
to even come across.
- Justin, that's a lot of
money.
- Justin Uhart,
deal or no deal?
[audience exclaiming]
- Keep on rolling.
- That's a nice looking board.
- Four huge ones still
up there.
- Keep on going.
- Thanks, but no thanks.
- So, I came here with
a number, a magic number,
and I have to have at least
six figures before I'm out.
Do you hear that, banker?
At least six figures before
I'm going anywhere.
[cheers and applause]
- No deal.
- Oh.
- How does that feel?
- I got a little feeling in
my gut right there.
That just kinda hit me.
- You know, you've inspired
everybody in this room.
You saved the life of
a young lady.
[cheers and applause]
You inspire other people.
You inspire your friends,
you inspire your sister,
you inspire this audience,
you inspired the world.
But we wanna help you
a little bit.
Would you like to be inspired?
- Absolutely.
What's gonna happen?
You're making me nervous--
- So, I'd like to say
to this hero,
I want you to meet your hero.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh.
Oh.
- Emmitt Smith.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my God.
- How you doing?
- Good to meet you.
- Oh, man.
- Dude.
- Awesome.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yes, sir.
- Boom.
- Whoo.
Oh, yes.
- Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
- Emmitt Smith!
[cheers and applause]
Are you staying with us
for a little bit?
- Yeah, I'll hang here.
I mean, he's doing so well,
I just don't wanna jinx it.
- I'm a little choked up,
honestly.
You're Emmitt Smith.
You were my childhood idol.
Cowboys have been my team
ever since I was a kid,
and you're the man.
- Thank you.
- I'm so stoked you're here.
Now let me just say this
to you.
Oftentimes--
oftentimes as athletes,
we get chosen as heroes
of other people.
But the reality of the fact is,
we are out there entertaining
people
and inspiring people to
their level of greatness.
But when you save
a person's life
under circumstances
that you were under...
Nobody else could ever question
to me what a hero truly is.
- Thanks, man.
- The men and women who save
lives and protect our country
the way you do,
y'all are true heroes, bro,
true, true heroes.
- Thanks a lot, man.
- And for being who you are,
I wanna invite you and a guest
to come join me and my wife
at the Emmitt Smith
Invitational out of Dallas
for a weekend of fun
with all the celebrities
that's gonna be at
the golf tournament
and to join ourselves
at the gala.
So...
- Absolutely.
Yes, yes, I'll go.
- So, we can kick it again,
and I look forward to it.
Now let's go get this
million dollars.
- Let's win.
Yes!
- Thanks, Emmitt.
- Emmitt Smith!
- Thank you, bro.
- Boom.
- Look at that.
- [chuckles]
- Thank you.
- Now I'm fired up now.
Let's keep going.
Three cases to open.
- Ten.
- I feel a new energy here.
- Vaeda, you feel it?
- I feel it,
let's keep it going.
- Open your case.
- Left side.
- Left side, here we go.
♪ ♪
- Be the penny.
- Oh.
- Ooh.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
- You believe the million
dollars is in your case.
The million dollars is still
on the board.
- It's up there.
- Two more cases to open.
- Three.
- Yeah.
- Here we go.
- Okay, Katie.
- I'm waiting for
those pennies.
- Gotta keep it low.
- Yes.
- Keep it low.
- Open the case.
♪ ♪
- Yeah!
- That's good.
[cheers and applause]
- That is really good.
One more case.
[applause]
- Five, please.
- Five.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Lani.
Okay, look at that board.
There's one case
holding a million dollars
and one unopened case
in this round.
We'll find out if it's in
that case when we come back.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
announcer:
$1 million still in play.
- That $1 million
is kinda standing alone.
- Yeah, it's huge.
announcer:
Justin holds on strong...
- Yeah.
[cheers and applause]
announcer: While the banker
tries to command the game.
- And, uh, I wanna just--
- Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
So Kim, you going
for our big Drive Safe
& Save discount?
Yup! Using the app.
I've been quite vigilant.
Ahh! Easy, easy!
But you're in labour...
Don't mess
with my discount!
(Clearing throat)
Get a discount up to 30%
with Drive Safe & Save.
After walking six miles at
an amusement park...
Get a discount up to 30%
Bill's back needed a
vacation from his vacation.
So he stepped on the
Dr. Scholl's kiosk.
It recommends our best
Custom Fit Orthotic
to relieve foot, knee, or
lower back pain.
So you can move more.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to move.
(Steel-drum ringtone sounds)
Hello?
Hello there!
Almond Joy is Tropi-Calling!
When you need a taste
of vacation,
pick up!
♪♪
Every day,
visionaries are creating
the future.
♪♪
So, every day,
we put our latest technology
and unrivaled network to work.
♪♪
The United States
Postal Service makes
more e-commerce
deliveries to homes
than anyone else
in the country.
♪♪
Because the future only
happens with people
who really know how
to deliver it.
[exciting music]
Because the future only
happens with people
[cheers and applause]
- Welcome back to
"Deal Or no Deal."
I'm Howie Mandel,
this is Justin Uhart,
a hero from Vegas.
His hero is here...
Emmitt Smith.
That's so amazing.
What a surprise that was.
You have one more case to open
before the next offer.
Are you nervous?
- Uh, feelin' it,
I'm super nervous.
- Because that $1 million
is kinda standing alone.
- It's there, it's huge.
- You picked number five
before the break.
I hope you got something
in there, like,
a penny or a dollar.
Something--anything from
the left side.
- Lani...
Open that case.
♪ ♪
- Oh, no.
- Okay, the million's still in.
The million is still in.
You have a 25% chance
of walking out of here
with 300,000
or a million dollars.
Right?
Think of those odds.
[phone ringing]
[audience booing]
Hello.
- Well, ought to be in
six figures right now
on the offer.
- Okay.
- She's mean.
- The offer gotta be 150.
- Obviously, you knocked out
a big amount of money.
The offer went down.
- Hmm.
- Tough game.
Emmitt, you know what
pressure is like
in the middle of a game.
- Yes, I do.
- Do you have a philosophy
about pressure
when you're playing a game?
- Yep, tune all the noise out.
Zone in on your numbers
and go for it.
- Yeah.
- Whoo.
- That's right, baby.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Those are words from
your hero.
The new offer is $60,000.
[audience booing]
You have not counter-offered
yet.
You have a counteroffer.
- Look at--he still has 50
and he still has 75,
so the offer is still
on the board.
- That penny is making me
real, real nervous,
but I'm also saying "no deal,"
'cause we got Emmitt Smith
on our side.
- Whoo.
- [laughs]
- That's a lot of pressure
on you.
- That's right.
That's right.
- All right.
- Justin Uhart,
deal or no deal?
[audience exclaiming]
- [screams]
- No deal.
No deal.
[cheers and applause]
- You go with your gut.
You seem to be a guy
that goes with the gut.
During that Vegas tragedy,
you went with your gut.
Most people probably
would have just run.
And you gut was
"I'm gonna stay there,
and I'm gonna save a life."
- You had to.
I mean, the emotion of having
a great concert
and your friends,
and then all of a sudden it
just--all hell breaks loose,
really messes with you.
And when I was running,
I saw her on the ground,
like, she needed help.
There's no way I could have
ran away.
- Uh...uh, I wanna just--
- Oh, my God.
Jan.
- Oh.
[cheers and applause]
It's Jan.
- This is the woman whose life
he saved.
- Sorry I didn't get to tell
you I was coming.
- This is the woman that was
lying on the ground bleeding.
He stopped
and he saved her life.
[cheers and applause]
- Whoo.
- Is it okay if I hold?
- I'm just blown away
right now.
- This is one of the bravest,
kind-hearted young men
you'll ever meet.
And being able to be here
for him today
just means the world.
This is my hero.
- Yeah.
- My hero.
Right here.
[applause]
[sighs]
You got this.
- All right.
- Let me just help her
into a seat.
I'm gonna put her right up
front here.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
[cheers and applause]
- Go get 'em.
- Thanks.
- Thank you so much for coming.
How does that make you feel?
- Man, you are throwing me
through
a whirlwind of emotions
right now.
You bring Emmitt Smith,
you got my best friends,
you got a million dollars
still in play
with beautiful girls.
Now what am I supposed to do?
- It's all you, don't say me
You.
- This is all you.
- It's going all around.
Two cases.
- Right.
- [exhales deeply]
24.
- That's Kizzi.
Kizzi, what a night, huh?
- Oh, my gosh, I'm so nervous.
Justin, you, obviously,
changed someone's life.
I hope tonight we can
change yours.
- Wow.
- Keep it low for me, please.
- Open the case.
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
[audience groans]
- ans]
Aw, that hurt.
- Okay, but let me tell you
something.
You said that you talked
to your friends and your sister
out getting it to
six figures.
- Yes.
- $100,000 and you would be
out of here?
- Yeah.
- This is three times that,
is still in play.
[cheers and applause]
So, as disappointing
as that is,
tell me what it would mean
if you walked out
with sixes.
- That's a home.
$100,000 is a great amount of
money to anybody.
- Okay, one more case to open
in this round
before the next offer.
- Two, please.
- That's Taylor.
[applause]
To me, this case...
Be with your heroes,
be with your family,
everybody's in the room,
I feel the vibes.
This has gotta be good.
Taylor, anything but
the $300,000.
Open that case.
- Come on, come on.
- Penny, penny, penny, $1.
Any of those numbers
on the left.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
- All right.
- Ok
- Playing with some fire
right now.
- You are playing with fire.
- Mmm.
- Lot of it.
[phone ringing]
- Nervou  - Yeah, ve,
and she's laughing up there.
[phone ringing]
- I don't think she's laughing.
She's just a businessperson.
- Hello.
♪ ♪
Okay, all right.
She said the she is starting
to get the feeling
that your case is holding
the one penny.
- Wow.
- There's as much of a chance
of it holing the penny
as it can possibly be holding
$300,000.
There's a lot at stake.
- A lot at stake.
[applause]
- The offer dropped.
- It did?
- Yes.
The good news is if you don't
take the offer
and you wanna play on
or you counter
and she rejects it
and you play on,
you're only opening one case
at a time.
You'll have a five out of six
chance of opening
anything but the $300,000.
So, think about that
as I tell you the new offer
is $39,000.
$39,000, Justin Uhart...
Deal or no deal?
- [clears throat]
- How do you feel?
- Oscar, man, like,
what do I do here?
- It is a lot of money.
We still have a counteroffer
in the back of our pocket,
though.
- That's what I'm playing with
too.
Do we counter?
- There's not a losing
situation here right now.
Think about where you are.
Think about the people
that you have here right now.
You can't lose tonight.
[applause]
- Okay, Jan, I gotta ask you
too.
Do I keep going?
- Yes.
- Keep it going?
- Howie...
- No.
- I'm already a winner,
so I'm gonna keep going.
No deal.
- No deal.
[cheers and applause]
300,000 still in play
when we come back.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
announcer:
Justin's on a mission to
take home six figures.
- Yes!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I told you, I'm not leaving.
announcer: And Emmitt Smith
helps call the plays.
- We're moving into
the red zone,
so every decision right now
is very critical.
Stay away from 21.
- 21.
- Ooh, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
He literally just said,
"Stay away from 21."
- [laughs]
- I am so scared.
♪ ♪
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
(MEG VO)
I can see if my endometriosis
pain gets better...
Or I can...
(SHERRY VO)
I can just suck it up...
Or I can...
(DIANE VO)
I can tell myself tomorrow
will be different...
Or I can talk to
my gynecologist today!
(AVO)
You didn't choose to have
endometriosis...
but you can choose to ask
if ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA is specifically
developed for women
with moderate to severe
endometriosis pain.
In clinical trials,
ORILISSA was proven to reduce 3
common types of
endometriosis pain,
painful periods,
pelvic pain in between
periods,
and pain with sex.
Don't use ORILISSA if you are or
may be pregnant,
have osteoporosis,
severe liver disease, or are
taking drugs like
cyclosporine or gemfibrozil.
It may cause abnormal
liver tests.
ORILISSA may change your
periods, making it hard
to know if you are pregnant.
It does not prevent pregnancy.
Use birth control that does not
contain hormones.
ORILISSA may cause suicidal
thoughts or actions.
It may also cause bone loss.
Ask your gynecologist if
ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA. Made for endo pain.
Hey!
(Mixed chatter)
Look what we got!
So fluffy!
Mmmm!
You want that one?
I do too.
♪ Oh baby you ♪
♪ You got what I need ♪
♪ You got everything I need ♪
♪ Your love will never go away ♪
♪ 'Cause you ♪
♪ Oh you got what I need ♪
Amazon's got
everything you need
and free shipping for all.
Welcome, everyone.
TO BE NOBODY BUT YOURSELF IN A
WORLD WHICH IS DOING IT'S BEST
TO MAKE YOU EVERYBODY ELSE...
♪ ♪ ♪
MEANS TO FIGHT
THE HARDEST BATTLE,
WHICH ANY HUMAN BEING
CAN FIGHT AND NEVER STOP.
DOES THIS SOUND DISMAL?
IT ISN'T.
♪ ♪ ♪
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL LIFE ON EARTH.
♪ ♪ ♪
[exciting music]
IT'S- Welcome back to
WON"Deal Or No Deal."TH.
This is Justin Uhart.
I gotta tell you something,
I am drained.
When you hang with heroes,
it's very draining.
You're a hero.
Emmitt Smith is a hero.
- Oh, yeah.
- You know what?
Just coming here makes you
very heroic too.
This is the lady that he saved
in Las Vegas.
So, look at that board.
The biggest amount
is still in play
at $300,000.
[cheers and applause]
What did you say you wanted
to leave here with?
- Six figures.
- $100,000.
- 100,000.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Stay away from 21.
- Here we go.
- One case to open.
- 21.
- Ooh, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Well, wait, wait, what?
- [laughs]
- What did you just say?
- He literally just said,
"Stay away from 21."
- [laughs]
- So, now you have a decision
to make.
- Now do I switch?
Do I listen to Emmitt Smith?
♪ ♪
- My gut--I gotta go with
my gut.
- Go for it.
- You said--you said "Ignore
all the outside things."
- Yes, I did.
Yes, I did.
- Just do it.
- Yes, I did.
- That's right.
- Did you mean even if you're
the outside thing?
- I can't believe I just said
I'm ignoring Emmitt Smith.
- I know.
Ignore your hero.
[laughter]
Where is the penny?
Where is that penny?
- It's 21.
- You got it.
- That's Malika.
I am so scared.
- You're scared?
I'm scared.
- Malika, open the case.
- You can't turn around.
- Come on, go low, go low,
go low.
- Not 300, not 300, not 300.
- Yeah!
[cheering and applause]
Yes!
Oh.
Oh, my God!
- Yeah!
Yes!
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Whoo.
- You earned it.
- All right.
That's why we play.
both:
Boom.
- Boom.
- That was based on
your advice, Emmitt.
He zoned you out.
- Exactly.
- 'Cause you told him to.
- 'Cause you have to do
what you feel.
[phone ringing]
- That was good.
That was good.
- [laughs]
- That was good.
You gotta relish the moments.
- Oh, my God.
- Let her cool down
for a little bit.
- [laughs]
- "Let her cool down."
[laughs]
- Ready?
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
- All right.
Hello.
- Way up, way up.
- Oh, she said she's ready
to play
against you, Emmitt, anytime.
- [laughing]
- She asks, she might receive.
[laughter]
- Okay.
She said...you took a risk,
and with risk...
- Comes reward.
- There's reward.
- Yes.
- Yay.
[cheers and applause]
- Okay.
- The new offer is $49,000.
- Counter--counter 75?
- One case to open.
You have a four out of five
chance of opening
anything but the $300,000.
What does Vegas say?
- We need six figures, so...
- And it's--
- You could counter.
- And it's one case at a time.
- We're moving into
the red zone,
so every decision right now
is very critical.
- Mm-hmm.
- You came in with a game plan,
you got 19 in your hand.
You got some ugly numbers
up there on the board.
[laughter]
So, let's just knock 'em down,
and if you believe in 19,
you believe in 19.
- That's right.
That's right.
- Keep it going.
[cheers and applause]
- All right.
Justin Uhart, deal or no deal?
[audience exclaiming]
- I'm feeling so good, Howie.
I'm gonna go one more round.
- One more round.
- No deal!
- No deal.
[cheers and applause]
Oh, my God.
- [shrieks]
- One more, pick the case.
- Oh, my gosh, 14.
- Okay.
- Fourteen's a good number.
- All right, all right.
- That's a good number.
- That's Olga.
This is a big gamble.
Olga...
- [exhales deeply]
- Open your case.
- $1.
♪ ♪
- Good vibes, good vibes,
good vibes.
♪ ♪
- Yes!
- Yeah.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
[cheers and applause]
- Wow.
- You're doing good.
- That's what I'm talking
about.
[cheers and applause]
I told you, I'm not leaving.
- Offer.
- Ooh.
Ooh.
- Hello.
♪ ♪
Okay.
- All right.
- [sighs]
- That was a heavy, heavy sigh.
- I know.
She has decided to reward you.
And she' going to
reward you...
With your highest offer.
- Ah!
- We got this.
- Yeah.
- There's 300,000, an offer,
and a possible counteroffer.
We will clear the table
when we come back.
- [groans]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- At Universal Studios,
Justin transforms his game
to help him battle the banker.
- My name is Optimus Prime.
- Hold it.
High-five, you the man.
- Earthlings, roll out.
- Roll out.
We got no free pass.
Everything we have,
we've earned.
The unmistakable Lexus IS.
Lease the 2019 IS 300 for
$329 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
GLAD YOU'RE BACK
HOW YOU FEELING?
♪ ♪ ♪
(BOTH) EXHAUSTED.
BUT FINALLY BEING ABLE TO MAKE
THAT VOLUNTEER TRIP HAPPEN
WAS... AWESOME.
AWESOME.
YOU HAVE TO SCRUB.
WHAT DO THEY...
THEY USE FOR WASHING.
♪ ♪ ♪
LET'S DO IT EVERY YEAR.
WE'LL DO IT EVERY YEAR.
I THOUGHT YOU'D SAY THAT -
LET'S DO IT.
♪ ♪ ♪
SEE HOW INVESTING WITH A J.P.
MORGAN ADVISOR CAN HELP YOU.
VISIT YOUR LOCAL CHASE BRANCH.
IF YOU HAVE A GARDEN YOU KNOW,
WEEDS ARE LOWDOWN
LITTLE SCOUNDRELS.
DON'T STOOP TO THEIR LEVEL.
DRAW THE LINE WITH THE
ROUNDUP SURE SHOT WAND.
IT EXTENDS WITH A
PROTECTIVE SHIELD
AND TARGETS WEEDS
MORE PRECISELY.
IT LETS YOU KILL WHAT'S BAD
RIGHT DOWN TO THE ROOT
WHILE GUARDING THE GOOD.
ROUNDUP SURE SHOT WAND.
GOT WEEDS IN YOUR GRASS TOO?
TRY ROUNDUP FOR LAWNS.
KILLS WEEDS, NOT THE LAWN.
ROUNDUP BRAND.
TRUSTED FOR OVER 40 YEARS.
[knocking]
♪
Memories.
What we deliver by delivering.
[farmers bell]
(Driver)
Relax, it's just a bug.
That's not a bug,
that's not a bug!
(Burke)
Hit and Drone.
Seen it, covered it.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
I have a vision
correction number,
But I'm more than a number.
When I'm not sharing ideas
with my colleagues
I'm defending my kingdom.
My Essilor lenses offer more
than vision correction
with three innovative
technologies
For my ultimate in vision
Clarity
And Protection
Together in a single lens:
The Essilor Ultimate
Lens Package.
So, I can do more
of what I love!
Buy two pairs of
Essilor's best lenses
and get a $100 back instantly.
See more. Do more. Essilor
[exciting music]
- Wow, welcome back.
This is Justin Uhart.
I just wanna say you're a hero;
your hero is here,
Emmitt Smith;
and the person that you are
a hero to is right here,
the lady you saved.
- Hey.
[cheers and applause]
- We're at a pivotal part
of the game.
There is maybe $300,000
at stake.
The highest offer so far,
before this, was $76,000.
- So, is it gonna be 76.5?
- Come on, higher, Emmitt.
- 77?
- Howie, you're killing us
here.
- How am I killing you?
- 'Cause I need you to tell me.
- [laughs]
- Hush up.
- The offer...
- Yes?
- Is $82,000.
[cheers and applause]
- So, I think we're still in
the same position
as the last offer.
I mean, it's a great offer,
don't get me wrong.
I'd say no deal.
- Mmm.
- One case to open.
- We have that counter.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, we do.
- Counter.
- So...
- Get your six figures.
- If we decide to counter...
- Uh-huh.
- How high am I gonna push it?
- [sighs]
- 100, why not?
- I think six.
- If you decide to counter,
and she rejects the counter,
you still have to open up
on case.
- What if you counter it
to your 100,
if she says no then you're just
gonna pick another case,
and then you'll be up anyways.
- So, I'm gonna ask you,
Justin Uhart...
Deal or no deal?
- I would like to do
a counteroffer.
- There you go.
- Counteroffer.
- Be realistic.
- $105,000.
You said--you know,
it's interesting to hear
the mentality of people.
'Cause you said, "I'd be happy,
I would walk out of here
with $100,000,"
as soon as you got
the six figures.
But then you said,
"Eh...five.
Five more."
$105,000.
[phone ringing]
- Oh.
- What?
[audience groaning]
- Hello.
- That was a little high.
- She's saying that's
a pretty big ask on your part.
- Yeah.
- I could smile.
[laughter]
- She's saying that's not
helping.
- [laughs]
- Only about numbers,
pure numbers, pure business...
- Yes.
- No emotion.
- Oh, gosh.
- I'm not a numbers guy...
But she is.
- Hmm.
- She said based on
your gameplay...
Based on your risk...
But mostly, based on
the odds...
She said...
"No deal."
[audience groaning]
- Ooh.
- All good.
- Okay.
- All right.
- All right, here we go.
- Here we go.
- Whoo!
- One case.
[applause]
- Come on.
- [exhales deeply]
♪ ♪
Gosh, 26.
- Yes.
- Okay, that's Michelle.
- Okay.
- Whoo!
- $1.
- Show that dollar.
- You have to imagine
if Michelle
has something from
the left side
there's a good chance
it's going way up.
- It is.
- Come on.
- Here we go.
[cheers and applause]
- I am so nervous right now.
- Show him his fortune.
Open the case.
- You got it.
- I really hope it's
the dollar.
♪ ♪
[whispers]
Dollar.
- Come on, come on, come on.
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah!
- My boy.
- Oh, my God.
You're gonna do it.
- So smart, dude.
- [whooping]
Yes, sir.
- All right.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
- Ooh.
- Let it ring.
- Oh, yeah.
- [laughs]
Get that six figures.
♪ ♪
- We are really witnessing
heroics today.
A lot of risk, a lot of reward.
[applause]
She truly is respecting you,
but, you know, the more respect
and the harder into the game,
the tougher she becomes.
- [groans]
- Oh, come on.
- She's looking at this board.
You got a one out of three
chance
of having $300,000.
- Good odds.
[cheers and applause]
- Can you take the heat?
- I can take the heat, Howie.
- You think you can take
the heat.
You're ready to take the heat?
- He's calling you out.
- Or are you willing to take
$120,000?
- Yes! Yes!
[cheers and applause]
- There you go, baby.
There you go.
You got it.
- Remember:
There could be--you see
how much it went up,
from $82,000 to $120,000.
Went up $40,000.
Do you go one more time?
There could be $300,000
in this fortune cookie.
- Take the deal.
- Justin Uhart,
deal or no deal?
- Deal!
[audience exclaiming]
[cheers and applause]
- You deserve that.
- Whoo!
Thanks, man.
- Justin, you did it!
- I did it.
- Oh, my God.
You did it!
- Whoo!
- Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
- We did it.
- You did it.
- Okay, come here.
- Whoo.
- Okay, Justin.
Well played. You're leaving
here with $120,000.
[cheers and applause]
No question about it.
But let's find out if you made
a good deal.
- All right.
- Yes.
- You sold this for $120,000.
This case was worth...
You made a good deal.
Open those cases.
- Oh, man.
- There's the $1.
That's okay.
- You're good.
- You did good, buddy.
You played it right.
I wouldn't have gone on.
That's it!
Thanks to Jan Lambourne,
Emmitt Smith.
He's gonna be taking Justin
to a celebrity invitational
golf tournament.
Justin Uhart picked the case
based on a fortune cookie,
and he's walking out of here
with $120,000.