SUBSCRIPTIONS OF THE WORLD FOR
THEIR PRODUCTS SO I DO THINK IT
MAKES SENSE AND THE WORLIS BIG
ENOUGH FOR MULTIPLE OF THESE
THINGS AND AS I WAS SAYING
BEFORE, IT'S NOTOR BREAK
FOR APPLE.
THEY CAN PLAY THE LONG GAME, BE
IN THE MARKETS AND SEE HOW IT
DEVELOPS WITEIR CUSTOMER
RELATIONSHIPS.
>> ANOTHER ONE TO WATCH, AFTER
ALL THE DRAMA AND BACK AND
FORTH, NIKE CLOSEDHE DAY
HIGHER AFTER THAT SHARP DROP ON
THE AVENATTI TWEET
BEFORE HE WAS TAKEN INTO
CUSTODY.
WHAT A WEIRD STORY.
>> THAT DOES IT FOR TODAY.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
>> "FAST MONEY" BEGINS RIGHT
NOW.
>>> "FAST MONEY" STARTS RIGHT
NOW LIVE FROM THE NASDAQ MARKET
SITE IN NEW YORK CITY'S TIMES
SQUARE
I'M SCOTT WAPNER IN FOR MELISS
LEE.
TIM SEYMOUR, STEVE GRASSO, DAN
NATHAN AND GUY ADAMI
AHEAD ON "FAST," FINANCIALS
UNDER FIRE
THE GROUP SINKING DEEPER INTO
CORRECTION AS THE TEN-YEAR YLD
HITS ITS LOWEST LEVEL SINCE 2017
AND THE TOP CHNICIAN SAYS
THERE'S MORE PAIN COMING AND
WHAT TO BUY INSTEAD.
THE DOW ON TRACK FOR ITS FIRST
DOWN MONTH OF THE YEAR
MORE VOLATILITY,UY SAYS THIS
STOCK RIGHT HERE COULD BE ABOUT
TO BREAK OUT BUT WE START WHERE
ELSEAPPLE.
HOSTING A STAR-STUDDED EVENT
WITH A NEW STREAMING SERVICE,
GAMING SERVICES AND CREDIT CARD.
JOSH LIPTON HAS MORE FROM
CUPERTINO.
>> THE STAR OF THE SHOW HAD TO
BE THAT NEW VIDEO STREG
SERVICE.
IT'S CALLED APPLE TV PLUS.
>> WE PARTNERED WITH THE MOST
THOUGHTFUL ACCOMPLISHED AND
AWARD-WINNING GROUP OF CREATIVE
VISIONARIES WHO HAVE EVER COME
TOGETHER IN ONE PLACE  CREATE
A NEW SERVICE UNLIKE ANYTHING
THAT'S BEEN DONE BEFORE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
APPLE TV PLUS.
>> SO THIS NEW SERVICE, SCOTT,
WILL FEATURE ORIGINAL SHOW,
MOVIES AND DOCUMENTARIES FROM
HOLLYWOOD SUPERSTARS WHO WE
HERE TODAY TALKING ABOUT THEIR
NEW SHOWS, SO YOU SAW STEVEN
SPIELBERG, REESE WITHERSPOON,
JENNIFER AN 'TIS STO-- ANISTON D
OPRAH.
WHAT IS THE PRICE GOING TO BE OF
THIS SERVICE
WE'LL HAVE TO WAIT TORE THAT
DIONLY APPLE DEBUTED AN
CAN SCRIBE TO HBO, SHOWTIME AND
STARZ AND NEWS PLUS, A NEW
SUBSCRIPTION SERVICE BRINGING
OVER 300 MAGAZINES ANDEANG
NEWSPAPERS FOR 9.99, AN APPLE
CARD WHICH IS A NEW CARD BUILT
INTO THE APPLE ON THE iPHONE AS
WELL AS A PHYSICAL CREDIT CARD
DESIGNED TO WORK WHERE APPLE PAY
IS NOT ACCEPTED AND FINALLY
APPLE DID TEASE A NERVICE
FOR GAMERS AS WELL
IT'S GOING TO BE APPLE CAR CADE.
A SUBSCRIPTION SERVICE THAT WILL
FEATUROVER 100 NEW AND
EXCLUSIVE GAMES THAT ALSO
LAUNCHING IN THE FALL.
APPLE, OF UR, DOES BOTH A
HUGE INSTALL BASE, 1.4 BILLION
APPLE DEVICES OUT THERE SO HOW
MANY FANS CAN NOW APPLE CONVINCE
TO BUY IN TO THESE NEW SERVICES
VEILED TODAY
SCOTT, BACK TO YOU
> THANKS SO MUCH
APPLE SHARES CLOSING DOWN MORE
THAN 1%.
STILL UP AROUND 20% THIS YEAR,
SO WILL THE COMPANY'S
TRSFORMATION TO SERVICES PAY
OFF FOR INVESTORS?
THAT'S THE KEY QUESTION.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS ABOUT.
>> IT IS
THE STOCK IS UP 33% FROM JANUARY
2nd WHEN THE COMPANY
PREANNOUNCED PRETTY
DISAPPOINTING SCAL QUARTER
A LOT HAD TO DO WITH HARDWARE
AND WEAKNESS IN CHINA.
IF YOU CAN OVERLOOK ALL THAT AND
LOOK AT THE ANNOUNCEMENTS THEY
MADE TODAY WHILE THERE WASN'T A
WHOLE HECK OF A LOT OF DETAIL,
PRICG, THAT SORT OF THING,
WHEN THE PRODUCTS ARE GOING TO
BE RELEASED CAN YOU THINK ABOUT
THAT INSTALL BASE AND THE FACT
THAT THE AVERAGE iPHONE USER
SPENDS $44 ON -- YOU KNOW,
ANNUALLY ON THEIR -- THROUGH
THEIR DEVICE IN THIS ECOSYSTEM
AND THAT'S A WHOLE HOST OF
SERVICES THAT THEY'LL BE ABLE TO
EXPAND THAT ECOSYSTEM.
IT'S NOT A REASON TO BUY AT 188
BUCKS UP 33% FROM THOSE 52-WEEK
LOWS BUT SOMETHING THAT SHOULD
GIVE YOU SOLACE ABOUT THE FUTURE
OF THE COMPANY AS THEY TRY TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO OFFSET UNIT
DECLINES AND WHAT WILL
ULTIMATELY DECLINING MARGINS IN
THE HARDWARE BUSINESS.
>> TIMMY, DAN SAID IT.
NOT ENOUGH TO BUY THE STOCK.
IS THAT RIGHT?
>> AT 14 1/2 X TIMES CASH PUTS
YOU AROUND 220, 225.
I OWN THE STOCK.
I THINK IT'S WORTH OWNING
INDEPENDENT OF TODAY'S
ANNOUNCEMENT
I THINK I AGREE WITH DAN.
>> DO YOU BUY  FRE HERE?
>> YEAH, I CAN PUT FRESH CAPITAL
WORK HERE.
>> NOTHING BLUE YOU OUT OF THE
WATER.
THE SELL-OFF IS ABSURD
IF THAT'S WHY IT SOLD OFF, IT
FAILED AT 200.
>> MOVING DOWN INTO THE EVENT
ANYWAY.
>> THAT'S THE --
>> I MEAN TODAY, I MEAN.
>> THE GO TO ACTION.
YOU SELL IT BASICALLY ON THE
EVENT AND CHECK THE BOX AND DID
ENOUGH TO MAKE IT INTERESTING.
BUT IT'S NOT KILLING NETFLIX
PRICE ACTION SHOWS THAT.
IT'S HELPING ROKU.
I THINK THEY DID ENOUGH WITH
LEAVING --
SORRY
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
>> PRICE ACTION IN ROKU.
BENEFITS THEM, TAILWIND.
PRICE ACTION IN NETFLIX, NOT A
NETFLIX KILLER BUT APPLE IS NOT
A --
>> IT WILL BE INCLUDED SO APPLE
WILL BE INCLUDED ON ROKU'S
PLATFORM.
>> GUY, ATO YOU THINK,
CREDIT CARD, THE TV, THE CREDIT
CARD --
>> WELCOME
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU HERE.
>> YOU'RE ALWAYS WELCOMING
>> WELCOME BACK.
LET'S GET THOSE PLEASANTRIES OUT
OF THE WAY.
>> IT'S NICE.
>> LISTEN --
>> BACK TO THE MATTER AT HAND.
>> IT WAS A PRETTY INTERESTING
ANNOUNCEME GTING AWAY FROM
THE HARDWARE SIDE AND THINK IT'S
INTERESTING.
CREDIT CARD, PEOPLE WILL SAY,
NOA BIG DEAL
FOR A LOT OF MILLENNIALS IT
MIGHT BE
THEY'RE WORKING ON THAT INSTALL
BASE WITHOUT QUESTION.
IN TERMS OF THE STOCK, THOUGH,
ALL-TIME HIGH 232 OR SO IN
SEPTEMBER.
TRADED DOWN TO 1 -- WHAT WAS IT
142-ISH ON DECEMBER 24th
IF YOU LOOK AT THE 50%
RETRACEMENT PUTS YOU EXACTLY
WHERE IT'S TRADING RIGHT NOW
I HAPPEN TO WATCH THE "SQUAWK
BOX" WITH JOE KERNEN
HE INTERVIEWED JIM CRAMER.
NOT THAT I'M TRYING TO CURRY
FAVOR WITH JIM, JIM WAS DISMAYED
IT WAS HIGHER IN THE PREMARKET
SAYING IT WAS PERFECT TO SEL
OFF.
HE WAS RIGHT
I THINK IT BACKS OFFER
NOT TO SPAS ASPERSIONS AT APPLE.
I JUSTY IT'S RUN TOO FAR TO
>> I THOUGHT THAT WAS AN
INTERESTING THING.
SERVICE GROWTH IN THE QUARTER
WAS IN THE TEENS, YOU KNOW, IT'S
DECELERATED OFF OF WHAT WAS A
VERY SMALL BASE.
HIGHER GROWTH RATES AND 50% --
NOW THAT IT'S BECOME A $20
LLION ANNUAL BUSINESS AND
GROWING, IT'S MUCH LESS SO TO ME
I THINK THAT POINTING TO
SERVICES GROWTH IS NOT THE WHOLE
THING, YOU HAVE TO POINT TO THE
HIGHER MARGINS BUT YOU HAD A
GREAT DISCUSSION, THE HALFTIME
REPORT ON AT NOON EVERY DAY.
>> PROFESSIONAL.
>> BUT TONY SAID HE EXPECTS
UNITS TO BE DOWN 15% YEAR OVER
YEAR
THIS IS THE THIRD CONSECUTIVE
>> THAT'S REALLY --
>> YOU'LL NEED GREATER GROWTH
AND REALLY FAT MARGINS
THEY'RE SPLITTING --
>> IS IT ENOUGH?
>> IT AT LEAST GIVES YOU THE
CONVERSATION --
IT AT LEAST GIVES YOU THE
CONVERSATION AND GETS YOUR MIND
OFF THE HARDWARE BUSINESS THAT
IS SLUGGISH AND SLOWING AND
THINK ABOUT THE $40 BILLION
NUMBER
>> THEY SPENT TWO HOURS SPEAKING
TO THE ENTIRE WORLD ABOUT THIS
HUGE NEW OPPORTUNITY
WOULDN'T YOU LE WALL STREET
ANALYSTS TO COME OUT AND SAY
THIS IS GOING TO BE AN X AMOUNT
OF OPPORTUNITY
>> YEAH.
>> WE'LL --
>> THEY'RE NOT DOING THAT.
>> IF YOU THINK OF FIRST OF ALL
THE CREDIT CARD BUSINE, I
ACTUALLY THINK THAT IS SOMETHING
THAT ULTIMATELY COULD MOVE THE
NEEDLE
THE SERVICES BUSINESS, SORRY,
THE APPLE PLUS, THE TV PLUS AND
WHATEVER IS IN THAT BUNDLE AND
REALIZE THEY HAVE A FEW
HIGH-PROFILE CONTENT CREATOR ON
THEIR PLATFORM RIGHT NOW, LOOK,
IT'S GOING TO TAKE TIME.
THERE WAS NOTHING THEY COULD
HAVE TOLD THAWS WOULD HAVE
ANGED THE STORY.
THIS IS ABOUT A COMPANY
ALLOCATING RESOURCES TOWARD HIGH
MARGIN BUSINESSES AND AT THIS
POINT AND VALUATION WHY
SHOULDN'T WE BELIEVE APP
"JOURNAL" THEY'VE DELIVERED ON
EVERYTHING THEY WENT TO DO WITH
AN INCREDIBLY LOYAL CUSTOMER
BASE WHO -- THOSE GUYS PROBABLY
WANT --
FOR YEARS APPLE TV WAS
RELEASED EIGHT YEARS AGO OR
SOMETHING AND STEVE JOBS CALLED
IT A HOBBY
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN CATEGORIZED
THAT WAY
ROKU HAD A BIG DAY
>> EVERYTHING HAD A BIG DAY --
>> IT'S A VERY CONFUSING.
>> DOESN'T HAVE TO BE, DOES IT
>> THIS IS THE FIRST OFFERING
THIS COMPANY HAS EVER PUT OUT IN
E SOFTWARE UNIVERSE AT YOU
CAN GET WITHOUT THEIR HARDWARE
THERE'S SOME THINGS ON ANDROID
NOW.
ES ON THE ANDROID DEVICE
THAT IS A MASSIVE SHIFT FOR THE
COMPANY OVER THE 40-YEAR --
>> THEY HAVE TO.
>> I KNOW SO THE QUESTION IS,
THERE'S SO LITTLE DETAIL BIT
WHO KNOWS.
THIS MAY NOT B-- THE VIDEO
STREAMING BUSINESS MAY NOT --
>> IT WASN'T ENOUGH -- I'LL
SPEAK -- IT WASN'T ENOUGH FOR ME
TO SAY I'M ON BOARD.
FIRST OF ALL WE DON'T KNOW
PRICING OR WHAT THE OFFERING
WILL BE.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S ENOUGH
THERE BUT I DO OWN THE STOCK
I OWN IT FROM LOWER AND IF I OWN
TODAY. IS, IN EFFECT, BUYING IT
PUTTING NEW MONEY TO WORK
BECAUSE YOU'RE STILL STAYING
LONG SO I THINK THEY DID ENOUGH
TO PREOCCUPYPLE UNTIL WE GET
ALL THE DETAILS.
>> DOES IT GET YOU EXCITED ABOUT
WHAT THEY'RE DOING FROM THE
SERVICES STANDPOINT TO, AGAIN,
GROW THAT BUSINESS TO ENOUGH
SCALE TO OFFSET ANY SLOWDOWN IN
PHONES
>> LOOK.
>> AND HARDWARE.
>> DAN TALKED ABOUT HOW IT'S A
SMALL BASE SO THE EARLY GROWTH
NUMBERS OF THE DELTA WAS MORE
IMPRESSIVE A YEAR AND A HALF AGO
BUT IT'S STILL AN ABSOLUTE IN
TERMS OF AGGREGATE TERMS
MASSIVE.
I AM EXCITED ABOUT THE LOYALTY
AND ABOUT THE DIFFERENCE WAYS
THEY'RE MONETIZING
PEOPLE ARE COMMITTED TO APPLE
AND THEY'RE STUCK IF THEY'RE ON
TV AND I CAN PICK UP A KNICKS
GAME, $2.99 WON'T MEAN A LOT
A LOT BEHAVE THAT WAY WITH
APPLE.
>> THEY'RE NOT SAYING IT,
THEY'RE FOCUSING ON SERVICES AND
IT'S BECAUSE THEY SEE THE
DECELERATION IN HARDWARE
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO SAY THAT
BUT THEIR LASER FOCUS --
>> THEIR ACTIONS SPEAK LOUDER
THAN WORDS.
>> JINKS.
>> THE QUESTION, IS THE
SERVICE'S BUSINESS, ARE REVENUES
SLOWING TO THE POINT WHERE TIGHT
GO
-- IT'S GOING TO BE A
HINDRANCE?
YOU CAN'T HAVE SERVICE REVENUE
SLOWING AT THE SAME TIME THAT
HANDSET SALES ARE SLOWING?
>> IN ORDER TO GET THE VALUATION
THEY WANT THE PEOPLE ALONG THE
STOCK WATCH SERVICES REVENUE HAS
TO BE AROUND 20% TO 22%.
WHAT, ARE WE ABOUT 15%, 16%?
AND THAT IS GETTING SLOWER
TOWARDS THE UPSIDE
>> ONE POINT, IT'S REALLY
IMPORTANT.
YOU DON'T TEED TO HAVE HYPER
GROWTH
CAN YOU HAVE MIDTEENS GROWTH ON
A BUSINESS THAT'S, YOU KNOW,
THAT HAS MUCH HIGHER MARGINS
THAN THE HARDWARE BUSINESS
GREAT FOR THE OVERALL PIE.
THIS DOESN'T NEED TO BE A HYPER
GROWTH STORY BUT TAKING SOME OF
THE TOTAL ADDRESSABLE MARKET
THAT EXISTS AND GROWING IT ON
YOUR USER BASE THAT MAY NOT BE
USINOF SERVICES OF OTHER
PROVIDERS.
>> THE NEGATIVE WAY TO SPIN IT
FROM A PERSON LONG HOW MUCH ISTL
ABOUT TRYING TO STEM OR STOP THE
SLIDE IN HARDWARE SALES?
THEY'RE PUTTING AN AWFUL LOT OF
TIME INTO SERVICES
MAYBE THEY JUST CAN'T HANDLE THE
SLIDE -- THERE'S NOTHING TO DO
ABOUT THE HARDWARE SIDE WHICH
THEN BECOMES AN OVERWHELMING --
>> YOU HAVE TO TARGET YOUR
INSTALLED BASE, 1.BILLION
DEVICES IN THE UNIVERSE OUT
THERE.
>> I KNOW.
I'M THE INSTALL BASE TOO AND I
WASN'T OVERWHELMED BY THIS
THIS IS NOT GOING TO BE
SOMETHING THAT -- AT LEAST ALT
THIS POINT.
>> TIM WILL PLAY 3 BUCKS FOR A
KNICK GAME
>> THEY'RE WORTH A BUCK.
>> I WILL PAY 3 BUT THAT'S WHAT
PEOPLE DO ON THEIR iPHONES AND
THEY HAVE A CAPTIVE AUDIENCE
1.4 INSTALLED BASE
THE ULTIMATE IS PROBABLY 20
TIMES AS OPPOSED TO ABOUT 11
TIMES ON THE HARDWARE AND
SOMETHING PEOPLE FORGET ON A $4
BILLION -- IF.
>> YOU MENTIONED JAMIE DIMON
DIDN' -
CRAMER DIDN'T LIKE THE STOCK UP.
IT HAS RUN --
>> THIS STOCK USUALLY RUN HAS AN
EVENT AN SELLS OFFER
S
SAKINOCCI SAID ON THE SHOW --
>> THE MARKETPLACE TOLD YOU THE
VALUATION AND WEREN'T IMPRESSED
AND SOLD THE STOCK OFF AND ALL
RE RIVERALS WERE BOUGHT.
>> UP 10% IN A MONTH.
>> IT LAGGED THE MARKET TOO,
SCOTT.
THERE'S SOME PART THATENMENT
GOT SO PR AND PEOPLE WERE
LOOKING AT VALUATIONS AND APPLE
UNDERPERFORMED
>> MORE, CUPERTINO, GENE, YOU
WERE IN THE EVENT, I BELIEVE,
TODAY.
WHAT'S YOUR TAKEAWAY TONIGHT
>> SCOTT, REALLY TWO IMPACT.
IF YOU PUT THESE FOUR SERVICES
TOGETHER AND THINK ABOUT WHAT IT
COULD ADD IN THE NEXT FIVE YEARS
I THINK ABOUT A BILLION OR 20
BILLION OR SO IN REVENUE, THAT
PROBABLY EQUATES TO ABOUT 10% IN
"S
ANNUAL SERVICES GROWTHTHAT'SHE .
THEN I THINK THERE'S A HIGHER
LEVEL ORDER THAT APPLE IS
SHOOTING FOR THAT GETS LIN
THESE ANNOUNCEMENTS.
THEY'VE BEEN LARGELY ANTICIPATED
AND WHETHER OR NOT THE CONSUMERS
WANT THIS REMAINS TO BE SEEN BUT
EFFECTIVELY WHAT APPLE IS
SAYING, THEY'LL TAKE THINGS WE
INTERACT WITH EVERY DAY WHETHER
A SCREAMING SER-- STREAMING SERE
OR CREDIT CARD AND IT'S
ENRICHING PEOPLE'S LIVES AND I
RECOGNIZE WHEN I USE THAT
LANGUAGE IT MAKES ME FEEL LIKE
I'M JUST REPEATING WHAT THEIR
MESSAGE BUT I THINK IT IS AN
IMPORTANT DISTINCTION TRYING TO
CREATE CONTENT NOT ABOUT THE
TYPICACONTL T WE'VE SEEN, THIS
ENRICHED CONTENT, GAMING MORE
HEALTHY GAMING AND FIRST TIME A
CREDIT CARD CAN ACTUALLY ADD
TRANSPARENCY AND THAT GETS LOST
THE CONVERSATION TODAY.
THESE SUBTLE LITTLE APPROACHES
THAT APPLE DOES TO MAKE OUR
LIVES JUST A LITTLE BIT BETTER
AND I THINK THAT ULTIMATELY WILL
YIELD A HIGHER SHARE PRICE
I'M ENCOURAGED BY THE
ANNOUNCEMENT.
>> IT TAKES THE SERVICES
BUSINESS TO THE NEXT LEVEL, SO
TO SPEAK
>> YEAH, DEFINITELY ONHE VIDEO
SIDE, ON THE CREDIT CARD
WHAT THEY'RE DOING IS SOMETHING
THAT I THINK OTHER CREDIT CARDC
TRY TO ADD THAT LAYER OF
TRANSPARENCY
REALLY SHIFTING THE FOCUS FROM
MAKING MONEY AS AN ISSUER TO TRY
TO -- APPLE IS NOT GOING TO MAKE
A TON OF MONEY OFF THE CDIT
CARD
I WANT TO BE CLEAR ABOUT THAT.
THIS IN FIVE YEARS CAN BE CALL
IT A BILLION AND A HALF DOLLAR
BUSINESS, MUCH SMALLER THAN THE
$15 BILLION BUT THE INTERESTING
PART JUST TO GO ONE MORE LEVEL
DEEPER ON THE CREDIT CARD, THE
EXCITING PART, IF YOU LOOK AT
THE OTHER ANNOUNCEMENTS THERE
ARE VARIATIONS TO A BETTER
DEGREE THAWE'VE SEEN BEFORE
BUT THE CREDIT CARD, THAT
ACTUALLY WAS A MAMEASURABLE
I THINK THAT IS A GOOD EXAMPLE
OF WHAT AN ADVANTAGE THAT APPLE
HAS OF TYING TOGETHER THE
HARDWARE, SOFT AND SERVICES.
>> GENE, WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE
INVESTMENT THEY'RE PUTTING IN
AND TRYING TO BECOME A
COMPETITOR OF NETFLIX, WERE YOU
UNDERWHELMED BY THE AMOUNT OF
INVESTMENTS, SHOULD THAT BE 10X
OR THE FACT TO YOUR POINT IT'S
FOUR SERVICES SO THEY'RE TRYING
TO FOCUS ON ALL OF THEM AND NOT
JUST ONE OF THEM AND THEN MORE
OF AN AGGREGATOR VERSUS A DIRECT
COMPETITOR TO SO MANY SERVICES
THEY'RE OFFERING
>> I THINK THEY WANTED TO TRY TO
BUNDLE ALL THESE SERVICE
ANNOUNCEMENTS TOGETHER
A LOGICAL TIME OF THE YEAR TO DO
THAT
WHEN YOU DO THAT, YOU HAVE TO
PREANNOUNCE THINGS AND DON'T
HAVE A LOT OF DETAIL SO LET'S
TALK ABOUT THE VIDEO REAL
QUICKLY.
IT'S UNCLEAR HOW MANY SHOWS AND
MOVIES THEY HAVE
MOST LIKELY PROBABLY AROUND 40
WHICH IS A FAR CRY FROM NETFLIX
AT A THOUSAND ORIGINAL SERIES.
BUT I THINK THE QUALITY OF THIS
IS WHAT IS GOING TO ULTIMATELY
STAND OUT AND I SUSPECT THE WAY
APPLE WILL MEASURE THEIR SUCCESS
IS THE NUMBER OF INDTRY
AWARDS
I DON'T KNOW ENOUGH ABOUT
ENTERTAINMENT AND THE AWARDS
THEY'LL GUN FOR BUT AT THE
OF THE DAY THIS CONTENT, THIS
DIFFERENT APPROACH IS GOING TO
HAVE AN IMPACT AND THINK THAT
COULD BE A SIMILAR SIZE BUSINESS
AS NETFLIX CALLS IT, $15 BILLION
A YEAR
I AM IN THE CAMP IT WILL HAVE A
NEGATIVE IMPACT OVER THE NEXT
YEAR.
>> HOW DO YOU JUDGE THE STOCK
TODAY GIVEN THE FACT IT HAD SUCH
A BIG RUN INTO THE
ANNOUNCEMENTS?
>> I THINK IT'S A GREAT EXAMPLE
OF HOW THESE APPLE EVENTS SET
UP
WE GENERALLY KNOW WHAT'S
HAPPENING GOING INTO IT BUT THE
SIGNIFICANCE OF WHAT'S ANNOUNCED
REALLY DOESN'T BECOME MORE CLEAR
TO US UNTIL QUARTERS AND YEARS
AHEAAND I THINK I JUDGE THE
SIGNIFICANCE AS APPLE IS MAKING
A STATEMENT AND GOING AFTER
SERVICES BUT THEY'RE ALSO TAKING
A DIFFERENT APPROACH TO SERVICE.
THAT DIFFERENT APPROACH IS
ENRICHING LIVES AND MORE HEALTHY
GAME CONTENT
SO I VIEW THIS AS A POSITIVE IN
LINE WITH APPLE'S BRAND AND
MENTIONED SECURITY IF YOU'RE
INTERESTED AND PLAYING BUZZWORD
BINGO SEVEN TIMES THEY ARE HEAVY
ON THAT THEME AS WELL WHICH I
THINK IS SOMETHING UNIQUE APPLE
CAN ADD TO THESE SERVICE.
>> THIS MUST TAKE A DEAL FOR A
CONTENT COMPANY OFF THE TABLE.
>> WHAT WOULD -- WHAT WOD IT
TAKE TO -- I MISSED THAT.
>> I'M SAYING THESE KIND OF
ANNOUNCEMENTS WOULD TAKE A DEAL
FOR ANY KIND OF CONTENT COMPANY
BY APPLE OFF THE TABLE
>> I THINK LARGELY YOU'RE RIGHT
BECAUSE I THINK WHAT IT SHOWS
THEY WANT TO DO SOMETHING
DIFFERENT.
>> DO IT THEMSELVES.
>> I DON'T THINK THEY'LL ACQUIRE
NET FLISHGS.
CBS, THEY'LL ACQUIRE SOME TYPE
OF CONTENT
THEY WOULD HAVE TO KILL A LOT OF
THE CONTENT SO I THINK IT
LARGELY DOES TAKE THAT OFF THE
TABLE.
>> GENE, THANKS.
GOOD TO TALK TO YOU AS ALWAYS.
GUY.
>> BEGIN, GENE, HE NAILS IT.
50% RETRACEMENT OFF THE ALL-TIME
HIGH
THE 50 DAY MOVING AGE COMING
IN AROUND 175.
I THINK IT'S REASONABLE TO THINK
BEFORE EARNINGS ON APRIL 30th
APPLE RETESTS THAT 175 LEVEL.
>> I THINK THEY MISS THE MARKET
AS FAR AS VIDEO CONTENT.
THAT'S NOT WHY PEOPLE HAVE KNELT
APPLICATION AND NETFLIX AND
CHILL.
NETFLIX'S ORIGINAL CONTENT IS
LESS THAN 8% OF THEIR VIEWABLE
HOURS.
APPLE IS SO FAR AWAY
OPRAH TV ON APPLE TV WON'T BE
THE REASON WHY THE ECOSYSTEM
USES THEIR SERVICE SO THIS IS
GOING TO BE A DUD FOR A BID.
>>> BANK STOCKS GETTING CRUSHED.
GET A LOT WORSE FOR ONE KEY ULD
GROUP.
HE'LL BE HERE TO TELL YOU WHICH
ONE.
PLUS, TESLA IS SINKING AFTER RBC
SLASHES ITS PRICE TARGET ON THE
ELECTRIC CARMAKER.
THE STOCK JUST DID SOMETHING
THAT COULD SIGNAL A U-TURN AHEAD
AND LATER GUY IS STEPPING UP TO
THE PLATE WITH ONE STOCK HE SAYS