GUARANTEED WHAT YOU SEE RIGHT
HERE.
CLOSING THE BORDER ISN'T THE
FIX.
NEITHER IS BLAMING OTHERS.
US THAT EMERGENCY TOó DEAL WITH
THE REAL EMERGENCY.
SHOW THE DEAL MAKING POWER THAT
YOU BRAGLL THE■/■/.
GET THESE PEOPLE TO ACT.
YOU WANT TO GET MORE T THE
BASEó YOU, STOP MAKING
EXCUSES.
MAKE SOMETHING HAPPEN HERE.
YOUR PEOPLE ARE CRYING OUT FOR
HELP.
OTHERWISE, THE QUESTIONL
CLEARLY BECOME WHY DID YOU ALLOW
THIS TO HAPPEN.
IT'S TIME FOR THE MAN.
"CNN TONIGHT" WITH D. LEMON ON A
FRIDAY NIGHT, WHAT'S BETTER THAN
THAT?
NOTHING, MY FRIENDS.
>> PEOPLE CALL ME D. LEMON ON
THE STREETS ALL THE TIME.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
I CARRY YOU LIKE ATLAS CARRIES
THE GLOBE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
NOTHING.
I'M NOT GOING TO GO THERE.
>> WHAT WAS YOUR OLD NICKNAME?
>> I NEVER HAD AN OLD NICKNAME.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK.
>> WELL, MR. DON LEMON,
SUPERHERO.
SO I GOT TO TELL YOU --
>> PLEASE.
>> YOU SAID THE DEAL MAKING.
WASN'T THE DEAL -- REMEMBER THE
ORIGINAL DEAL THAT HE WAS
SUPPOSED TO MAKE?
>> NO.
>> MEXICO WAS GOING TO PAY FOR
THAT WALL.
>> OH, YES, THAT DEAL.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> IT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
>> THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
>> IT WAS BLUSTER, AND THE WALL
WAS A FARCE.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
LOOK.
I DON'T HAVE ANY PROBLEM WITH
THEM BUILDING PHYSICAL BARRIERS.
IT'S JUST NOT A PANACEA.
>> THERE'S ALREADY A PHYSICAL
BARRIER IN A LOT OF PLACE.
>> THERE IS, BUT, LOOK, THEY
NEED MORE.
IF THEY HAD MORE, THEY WOULDN'T
HAVE THE FLOW PROBLEMS THEY HAVE
RIGHT NOW.
I BELIEVE THAT.
BUT THEY NEEDED MORE THAN JUST
THAT.
AND YOU KNOW, TRIPP, ROY,
CICILLINE SAYS WE GAVE THEM THAT
STUFF TOO.
IT OBVIOUSLY WASN'T ENOUGH.
NOW I'M GOING TO GO DOWN THERE,
AND THEI GUARANTEE YOU THEY'RE
GOING TO SAY, WE NEED, WE NEED,
WE NEED.
EVERYBODY HERE IS TALKING ABOUT
LONG-TERM FIXES AND WE HAVE TO
HAVE A DEAL AND CONSERVATIVE
THIS AND LONG-TERM THAT.
DEAL WITH IT NOW.
GIVE THEM WHAT THEY NEED.
>> BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY CAN'T HE JUST BE HONEST
ABOUT IT?
WHY DOES HE HAVE TO LIE ABOUT
WE'RE ALREADY BUILDING THE NEW
SECTIONS OF THE WALL?
IT IS COMPLETELY, 100% NOT TRUE.
IT IS A LIE.
THERE'S NO NEW WALL THAT'S BEING
BUILT.
>> THERE WILL BE.
IF HE KEEPS SAYING IT LONG
ENOUGH, HE'LL BE RIGHT.
AND HE HAS TO DEFINE THEM AS A
BROWN MENACE.
HE HAS TO BE STRONG.
HE HAS TO TALK ABOUT CLOSING OFF
AND --
>> THAT'S NOT STRENGTH.
>> -- AND BEING TOUGH BECAUSE
THAT IS WHAT HE'S SELLING
PEOPLE.
HE CAN'T SAY WHAT WE'RE SAYING.
HE CAN'T SAY, LOOK AT THESE
FACES.
HOW CAN WE LET THEM BE LIKE
THIS?
LET'S FIND A BETTER WAY.
WE DON'T HAVE TO LET THEM ALL
IN, BUT WE HAVE TO TREAT THEM
ALL WITH CONNELL MPASSION.
THIS IS AMERICA, DAMN IT.
HE'S SELLING OUTRAGE.
>> THESE ARE YOUR WORDS.
HE'S TAKING YOU FOR A SUCKER.
>> AND HE'S HOPING YOU WILL
SWALLOW WHAT HE'S FEEDING YOU,
BUT IT'S A BAD DIET FOR
DEMO
DEMOCRACY.
>> THAT'S WHAT A CON MAN DOES.
>> THE CON MAN IS FOR
CONFIDENCE, AND THAT'S WHY HE
COMES AT YOU 100 EVERY TIME.
>> MANY PEOPLE FALL FOR THE LONG
CON EVERY TIME.
THANK YOU, SIR.
>> D. LEMON, MY MAN.
>> GREAT WEEKEND.■UIT.
>>> THIS IS "CNN TONIGHT."
I'M DON LEMON.
WHAT A WEEK IT HAS BEEN.
THINK ABOUT IT.
SUNDAY THE REPORT CAME OUT,
RIGHT?
THIS TIME LAST WEEK WE GOT OUR
FIRST LETTER FROM THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL, WILLIAM BARR, ON THE
MURALER INVESTIGATION SAYING IT
WAS COMPLETE.
THERE HAVE BEEN TWO MORE LETTERS
SINCE THEN.
THE LATEST ONE RIGHT HERE.
THE LATEST ONE JUST TODAY, ALL
RIGHT?
A LOT OF NEWS IN IT.
MUELLER'S REPORT EXPECTED TO BE
RELEASED TO CONGRESS AND THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE, TO THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE, BY MID-APRIL IF NOT
SOONER, OKAY?
BUT BARR IS SAYING THE PROCESS
OF REDACTING THE REPORT IS,
QUOTE, WELL ALONG AND THAT
MUELLER HIMSELF IS ASSISTING.
>> ALL OF THAT IS REALLY
IMPORTANT.
BUT IT ALSO RAISES A LOT OF
QUESTIONS.
A LOT.
AND SINCE WE DON'T YET HAVE
MUELLER'S FULL REPORT, A REPORT
THAT BARR WRITES IS NEARLY 400
PAGES LONG BY THE WAY, THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL'S LETTERS,
WELL, THEY'RE ALL WE HAVE TO GO
ON.
SO I WANT TO GO THROUGH THIS
LATEST LETTER IF YOU WILL ALLOW
ME POINT BY POINT BECAUSE
THERE'S SOME VERY IMPORTANT
INFORMATION IN THERE.
HERE IS HOW IT BEGINS.
IT BEGINS THIS WAY.
DEAR CHAIRMAN GRAHAM AND
CHAIRMAN NADLER, I WRITE IN
RESPONSE TO CHAIRMAN NADLER'S
MARCH 25th, 2019 LETTER AND
CHAIRMAN GRAHAM'S MARCH 27th,
2019 LETTER, WHICH ADDRESSED THE
INVESTIGATION OF SPECIAL COUNSEL
ROBERT S. MUELLER III AND THE
CONFIDENTIAL REPORT HE HAS
SUBMITTED TO ME.
HE'S REFERRING THERE TO NADLER'S
LETTER REQUIRING MUELLER'S FULL
REPORT TO BE RELEASED TO
CONGRESS NO LATER THAN APRIL
2nd, RIGHT?
THAT'S THIS COMING TUESDAY.
NADLER TODAY INSISTING THAT
DEADLINE STILL STANDS EVEN
THOUGH BARR IS APPARENTLY GOING
TO MISS IT.
HE'S ALSO REFERRING TO GRAHAM'S
INVITATION TO THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL TO TESTIFY BEFORE THE
SENATE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE.
SO BARR GOES ON TO SAY -- HE
SAYS, AS WE HAVE DISCUSSED, I
SHARE YOUR DESIRE TO ENSURE THAT
CONGRESS AND THE PUBLIC HAVE THE
OPPORTUNITY TO READ THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S REPORT.
WE ARE PREPARING THE REPORT FOR
RELEASE, MAKING THE REDACTIONS
THAT ARE REQUIRED.
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL IS ASSISTING
US IN THIS PROCESS.
SPECIFICALLY, WE ARE WELL ALONG
IN THE PROCESS OF IDENTIFYING
AND REDACTING THE FOLLOWING --
ONE, MATERIAL THAT BY LAW CANNOT
BE MADE PUBLIC.
TWO, MATERIAL THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMUNITY IDENTIFIES AS
POTENTIALLY COMPROMISING
SENSITIVE SOURCES AND METHODS.
AND THEN THREE, MATERIAL THAT
COULD AFFECT OTHER ONGOING
MATTERS INCLUDING THOSE THAT THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL HAS REFERRED TO
OTHER DEPARTMENT OFFICES.
AND, FOUR, INFORMATION THAT
WOULD UNDULY INFRINGE ON
PERSONAL PRIVACY AND
REPUTATIONAL INTERESTS OF
PERIPHERAL THIRD PARTIES.
LOTS OF REALLY IMPORTANT STUFF
THERE, OKAY?
BARR IS WELL AWARE OF ALL THE
DEMANDS FOR THE RELEASE OF THE
FULL MUELLER REPORT.
HE'S WELL AWARE THAT EVEN THE
PRESIDENT AGREES THE REPORT
SHOULD BE■■■■■AS■■>> MR.■■■■■■■T
INTENDS TO RELEASE THE MUELLER
REPORT IN FULL TO CONGRESS AND
THE PUBLI
DOú■ AGREE WITH THAT DECISION,
AND DO YOU WANT THE WHITE HOUSE
TO TAKE A LOOK OVER IT FOR
PRIVILEGE?
>> I HAVE GREAT CONFIDENCE IN
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL, AND IF
THAT'S WHAT HE'D LIKE TO DO, I
HAVE NOTHING TO HIDE.
>> SO IT'S NO SURPRISE THAT IN
JUST THE SECOND SENTENCE OF HIS
LETTER, BARR SAYS HE WANTS
CONGRESS AND THE PUBLIC TO BE
ABLE TO READ THE REPORT.
COMPARE THAT TO WHAT HE WROTE
LAST WEEK, SAYING HIS GOAL WAS
TO, QUOTE, RELEASE AS MUCH OF
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S REPORT AS
I CAN.
OKAY.
BUT BACK TO THE LETTER NOW.
BARR GOES ON TO LAY OUT FOUR
PRETTY BROAD CATEGORIES OF
MATERIAL TO BE REDACTED --
INFORMATION FROM THE GRAND JURY,
SENSITIVE INTELLIGENCE
INFORMATION, INFORMATION RELATED
TO ONGOING LEGAL MATTERS, AND
INFORMATION THAT WOULD INFRINGE
ON THE PRIVACY OF PERIPHERAL
THIRD PARTIES.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL HAS AN
AWFUL LOT OF DISCRETION THERE.
THE QUESTION OF EXACTLY WHAT
MUST BE REDACTED IN ANY OF THOSE
CATEGORIES IS FAR FROM BLACK AND
WHITE.
YOU'VE GOT TO WONDER JUST HOW
MUCH INFORMATION WILL BE BLACKED
OUT.
MUELLER USED THE GRAND JURY
EXTENSIVELY.
IN FACT, THEY'RE STILL WORKING,
SO THAT COULD MEAN A LOT OF
REDACTIONS RIGHT THERE.
CHAIRMAN NADLER RESPONDING
TONIGHT, SAYING, QUOTE, RATHER
THAN EXPEND VALUABLE TIME AND
RESOURCES TRYING TO KEEP CERTAIN
PORTIONS OF THIS REPORT FROM
CONGRESS, HE SHOULD WORK WITH US
TO REQUEST A COURT ORDER TO
RELEASE ANY AND ALL GRAND JURY
INFORMATION TO THE HOUSE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE AS HAS
OCCURRED IN EVERY SIMILAR
INVESTIGATION IN THE PAST.
THERE IS AMPLE PRECEDENT FOR THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE SHARING
ALL OF THE INFORMATION THAT THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL PROPOSES TO
REDACT TO THE APPROPRIATE
CONGRESSIONAL COMMITTEES.
AGAIN, CONGRESS MUST SEE THE
FULL REPORT.
OUR LEGAL EXPERTS ARE GOING TO
WEIGH IN ON THAT TONIGHT ON THIS
PROGRAM.
AND THEN THERE'S THE ISSUE OF
INTELLIGENCE INFORMATION.
HOUSE INTEL COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN
ADAM SCHIFF TWEETS THIS.
CONGRESS HAS ASKED FOR THE
ENTIRE MUELLER REPORT AND
UNDERLYING EVIDENCE BY APRIL
2nd.
THAT DEADLINE STANDS.
IN THE MEANTIME, BARR SHOULD
SEEK COURT APPROVAL JUST LIKE IN
WATERGATE TO ALLOW THE RELEASE
OF GRAND JURY MATERIAL.
REDACTIONS ARE UNACCEPTABLE.
FORMER DIRECTOR OF NATIONAL
INTELLIGENCE MR. JAMES CLAPPER,
HE'S GOING TO WEIGH IN ON THAT
TONIGHT.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL ALSO SAYS
THAT MUELLER HIMSELF IS INVOLVED
IN THE PROCESS OF REDACTING HIS
OWN REPORT, WHICH MAY GIVE BARR
SOME INSULATION FROM CRITICISM
IF HE CAN POINT TO MUELLER'S
INVOLVEMENT.
BUT BACK NOW TO TONIGHT'S
LETTER, OKAY?
AND THIS IS A QUOTE.
OUR PROGRESS IS SUCH THAT I
ANTICIPATE WE WILL BE IN A
POSITION TO RELEASE THE REPORT
BY MID-APRIL IF NOT SOONER.
ALTHOUGH THE PRESIDENT WOULD
HAVE THE RIGHT TO ASSERT
PRIVILEGE OVER CERTAIN PARTS OF
THE REPORT, HE HAS STATED
PUBLICLY THAT HE INTENDS TO
DEFER TO ME, AND ACCORDINGLY
THERE ARE NO PLANS TO SUBMIT THE
REPORT TO THE WHITE HOUSE FOR A
PRIVILEGE REVIEW.
NO PLANS TO SUBMIT THE REPORT TO
THE WHITE HOUSE.
BUT THAT IS FAR FROM AN
IRON-CLAD GUARANTEE, AND IT
DOESN'T RULE OUT BARR HIMSELF
RAISING EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE ON
THE PRESIDENT'S BEHALF.
AND THERE IS MORE.
QUOTE, ALSO I AM AWARE OF SOME
MEDIA REPORTS AND OTHER PUBLIC
STATEMENTS MISCHARACTERIZING MY
MARCH 24th, 2019, SUPPLEMENTAL
NOTIFICATION AS A SUMMARY OF THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL'S INVESTIGATION
AND REPORT.
FOR EXAMPLE, CHAIRMAN NADLER'S
MARCH 25th LETTER REFERS TO MY
SUP
SUPPLEMENTAL -- MY MARCH 24th
LETTER WAS NOT AND DID NOT
PURPORT TO BE AN EXHAUSTIVE
RECOUNTING OF THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S INVESTIGATION OR
REPORT.
AS MY LETTER MADE CLEAR, MY
NOTIFICATION TO CONGRESS AND THE
PUBLIC PROVIDED PENDING RELEASE
OF THE REPORT, A SUMMARY OF ITS
PRINCIPLE CONCLUSIONS.
THAT IS ITS BOTTOM LINE.
THE SPECIAL'S COUNSEL REPORT IS
NEARLY 400 PAGES LONG, EXCLUSIVE
OF TABLES AND OTHER INFORMATION.
400 PAGES LONG EXCLUSIVE OF
TABLES AND OTHER INFORMATION AND
ANOTHER APPENDICES.
AND SET FORTH THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S FINDINGS, HIS
ANALYSIS, AND THE REASONS FOR
HIS CONCLUSIONS.
EVERYONE WILL SOON BE ABLE TO
READ IT ON THEIR OWN.
I DO NOT BELIEVE IT WOULD BE IN
THE PUBLIC'S INTEREST FOR ME TO
ATTEMPT TO SUMMARIZE THE FULL
REPORT OR TO RELEASE IT IN
SERIAL OR PIECEMEAL FASHION.
NOT IN THE PUBLIC'S INTEREST TO
SUMMARIZE THE REPORT?
WELL, NOW HE TELLS US THAT.
IT IS TRUE THAT THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL CALLED HIS PREVIOUS
LETTER A SUMMARY OF ITS
PRINCIPAL CONCLUSIONS, NOT A
SUMMARY -- CALLED A SUMMARY OF
ITS PRINCIPAL CONCLUSIONS, NOT
JUST A SUMMARY.
BUT RATHER THAN DEBATE
SEMANTICS, WHY NOT JUST RELEASE
THE ENTIRE REPORT AND LET US
DECIDE FOR OURSELVES?
SO HERE'S HOW THE LETTER ENDS,
AND I READ FROM THE LETTER.
AS I HAVE DISCUSSED WITH BOTH OF
YOU, I BELIEVE IT WOULD BE
APPROPRIATE FOR ME TO TESTIFY
PUBLICLY ON BEHALF OF THE
DEPARTMENT SHORTLY AFTER THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL'S REPORT IS MADE
PUBLIC.
I AM CURRENTLY AVAILABLE TO
TESTIFY BEFORE THE SENATE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE ON MAY 1,
2019, AND BEFORE THE HOUSE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE ON MAY 2nd
OF 2019.
FINALLY, IN THE INTEREST OF
KEEPING THE PUBLIC INFORMED AS
TO THESE MATTERS, I INTEND TO
MAKE THIS LETTER PUBLIC AFTER
DELIVERING IT TO YOU.
SINCERELY, WILLIAM P. BARR,
ATTORNEY GENERAL.
SO THE ATTORNEY GENERAL SAYS
THAT HE IS AVAILABLE TO TESTIFY
ON MAY 1 AND MAY 2, WHICH IF THE
REPORT IS RELEASED, THAT WOULD
BE MID-APRIL AS PROMISED.
THAT WOULD BE TWO WEEKS LATER.
TWO WEEKS LATER.
THAT'S A REALLY LONG TIME TO
WAIT FOR THE ATTORNEY GENERAL TO
ANSWER QUESTIONS THAT WILL
UNDOUBTEDLY BE RAISED BY THIS
REPORT.
THAT'S A LONG TIME, A COUPLE
WEEKS.
BUT THE PRESIDENT ISN'T WAITING
FOR THE RELEASE OF THE REPORT.
HERE'S WHAT THE PRESIDENT
TWEETED TODAY.
THE PRESIDENT TWEETED TODAY, HE
SAID, MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST TAKE
OUR VICTORY AND SAY NO.
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF COUNTRY TO
RUN.
SO MUCH FOR DEFERRING TO THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL RIGHT THERE.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE SHOULD KNOW
WHAT'S IN THIS LETTER.
WE'VE GOT A LOT TO DISCUSS.
CNN'S EVAN PEREZ IS HERE.
LET'S BRING IN EVAN RIGHT NOW.
EVAN, HOW MUCH PRESSURE WAS THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL UNDER TO
RELEASE THIS REPORT TODAY?
>> WELL, I THINK THERE'S A LOT
OF PRESSURE.
I THINK YOU SAW THE DEMOCRATS,
CHAIRMAN NADLER, AND EVEN
LINDSEY GRAHAM HAVE BEEN TRYING
TO GET A LOT MORE INFORMATION
FROM THE ATTORNEY GENERAL.
I THINK THE DEMOCRATS HAD GIVEN
HIM APRIL 2nd AS A DEADLINE, AND
I THINK WHAT YOU'RE SEEING, DON,
IS THE ATTORNEY GENERAL TRYING
TO AT LEAST SHOW TO THE MEMBERS
OF CONGRESS THAT, LOOK, YOU'RE
GOING TO GET SOME ANSWERS.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET SOME ANSWERS
PERHAPS EVEN FASTER THAN I FIRST
INDICATED.
BUT LET THERE BE NO DOUBT.
I MEAN THE TWO SIDES ARE HEADED
TO A CONFRONTATION, RIGHT?
BECAUSE WHATEVER BARR RELEASES
IN MID-APRIL, IN A COUPLE OF
WEEKS, WILL NOT BE THE FULL
REPORT.
THERE WILL BE A LOT OF
REDACTIONS, SOME OF WHICH YOU
JUST LISTED THE FOUR CATEGORIES
OF THINGS THAT ARE GOING TO BE
REDACTED.
AND SO THEN THE FIGHT BEGINS.
AND I THINK THE DEMOCRATS HAVE
ALREADY POINTED OUT THAT THE
GOAL POSTS HAVE MOVED.
IT'S NOT JUST THE FULL MUELLER
REPORT THAT THEY WANT, BUT THEY
WANT THE UNDERLYING EVIDENCE.
THEY WANT TO SEE WHAT ELSE
MUELLER TURNED UP DURING THIS
22-MONTH INVESTIGATION, DON.
AND SO I THINK, AGAIN, A
CONFRONTATION IS COMING.
THERE'S GOING TO BE A SUBPOENA
EVENTUALLY PROBABLY, AND THEN
THIS IS PROBABLY GOING TO END UP
IN LITIGATION BEFORE A JUDGE.
>> NADLER'S NOT SATISFIED WITH
THIS RESPONSE.
SO WHAT IS HE SAYING?
WHAT ARE HIS CONCERNS?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
HE SAYS THAT THIS IS NOT ENOUGH,
AND HE WANTS -- STILL WANTS THE
FULL REPORT RELEASED
IMMEDIATELY, AND HE WANTS TO SEE
THE UNDERLYING EVIDENCE.
SO I THINK WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO
SEE IS THEY'RE GOING TO KEEP THE
PRESSURE UP ON THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL.
I THINK ONE OF THE THINGS THAT'S
HAPPENING RIGHT NOW, DON, IS THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT IS TRYING TO
MAKE SURE THAT THEY SEE -- THAT
THEY SHOW A UNIFIED FRONT.
SO YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE -- YOU
SAW BARR REFER TO SPECIAL
COUNSEL MUELLER STAYING ON TO
HELP WITH SOME OF THESE
REDACTIONS.
AND YOU HAVE ROD ROSENSTEIN, WHO
IS ALSO STILL IN THE BUILDING,
AND SO I THINK THE THREE MEN ARE
NOW BASICALLY TRYING TO SHOW A
UNIFIED FRONT TO THE MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS TO SHOW, LOOK, THIS IS
NOT JUST BARR'S INTERPRETATION
OF MUELLER, BUT THIS IS ALL OF
OUR WORK.
>> EVAN PEREZ, THANK YOU FOR
YOUR REPORTING.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
>>> THE ATTORNEY GENERAL HAS
WRITTEN THREE LETTERS IN A WEEK
ON THE MUELLER REPORT BUT THERE
ARE MORE AND MORE UNANSWERED
QUESTIONS.
WILL WE GET THOSE ANSWERS FROM
REDACTED?REPORT, OR WEY
to try.
New Infallible Full Wear
Concealer by L'Oreal.
With an extra-large applicator
and full-coverage
formula.
It shapes,
covers,
and contours.
So much more
than concealer.
■v1v1p1p1÷181414■>■á■á■>
w Infallible Full Wear
Concealer
g@■■Ñ=+u■ ñ■=ñ■■■ñ■■8■>■>■>ap■í■
So, you're open all day,
every day.
That's what 24/7 means, sugar.
Kind of like how you
get 24/7 access
to licensed agents with GEICO.
Hmm?
Yeah, you just go online,
or give them a call anytime.
You don't say.
Yep. Now what will it take
to get 24/7 access
to that lemon meringue pie?
PIE!
PIE'S COMING!
That's what it takes, baby.
After months of wearing
only a tiger costume,
GEICO®. Great service
from licensed agents, 24/7.
we're finally going on the
trip I've been promising.
Because with Expedia,
I saved when I added
a hotel to our flight.
♪
So even when she outgrows
her costume,
we'll never outgrow the memory
of our adventure together.
Unlock savings when
you add select hotels
to your existing trip.
Only when you book
with Expedia.
Behr presents: Tough as Walls.
♪
That's some great paint.
BEHR ULTRA, a top-rated
interior and exterior paint.
Paint, prime, protect -
all in one.
Now that's some great paint!
Find it exclusively
at The Home Depot.
>>> ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR IN A
LETTER TO CONGRESS RELEASED
TODAY SAYING HE IS WELL ALONG IN
MAKING REDACTIONS IN ROBERT
MUELLER'S REPORT AND EXPECTS TO
SEND IT TO CAPITOL HILL BY
MID-APRIL, IF NOT SOONER.
AND HE SAYS HE'S GETTING
ASSISTANCE ON THE REDACTIONS
FROM THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
HIMSELF.
A LOT TO TALK ABOUT.
MATTHEW ROSENBERG IS HERE, HARRY
LITMAN, AND GARRETT GRAFF.
GARRETT, I'M GOING TO START WITH
YOU.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL SAYS THE
MUELLER REPORT, A LITTLE OVER
400 PAGES.
EVERYONE WILL GET TO READ IT
THEMSELVES.
HIS PREVIOUS LETTER WAS NOT A
SUMMARY.
WHY DIDN'T HE SAY THIS FROM THE
VERY BEGINNING?
>> I THINK THAT'S A GREAT
QUESTION, AND ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT REALLY STRUCK ME IN READING
THIS LETTER WAS THERE WAS VERY
LITTLE IN IT THAT HE COULDN'T
HAVE SAID LAST FRIDAY OR ON
SUNDAY AND THAT IN SOME WAYS I
FIND IT SUSPICIOUS THAT WE'RE
LEARNING THESE ADDITIONAL
DETAILS ONLY NOW.
WE WOULD HAVE THOUGHT VERY
DIFFERENTLY ABOUT THE FRIDAY
LETTER OR THE SUNDAY SUMMARY,
WHICH HE IS NO LONGER CALLING A
SUMMARY, IF WE HAD KNOWN IT WAS
400 PAGES.
THIS IS A QUESTION I'VE BEEN
ASKING ALL WEEK.
I ASKED IT ON THIS SHOW EARLY IN
THE WEEK THAT, YOU KNOW,
LEARNING 65 WORDS OUT OF A
400-PAGE REPORT IS NOT REALLY
GETTING A GOOD SENSE OF WHAT IT
SAYS.
THIS IS, TO ME, SORT OF THE
HORSE THIEF SAYING, MAYBE IT'S
TIME TO CLOSE THE BARN DOOR
AFTER THE HORSE IS ALREADY GONE.
>> MATTHEW, DO YOU THINK BARR'S
TIMING -- YOU THINK IT WAS
INTENTIONAL?
IS HE TRYING FOR A RESTART HERE,
TRYING TO RESET THINGS?
>> I MEAN PERHAPS.
HE MAY JUST NOT BE GOOD AT
ROLLING OUT KIND OF MEDIA
STRATEGY HERE.
I THINK THERE'S A QUESTION OF,
YOU KNOW, WHY DIDN'T THEY HAVE
THIS THING READY TO GO WHEN THEY
ANNOUNCED THAT IT WAS DONE?
>> RIGHT.
>> THAT WOULD HAVE MADE A LOT OF
SENSE, WOULD HAVE ANSWERED A LOT
OF QUESTIONS.
I DO THINK THERE ARE PROBABLY
SOME PEOPLE AROUND THE PRESIDENT
THAT HAVE FIGURED OUT THAT WHILE
THERE MAY BE NO CHARGEABLE
CRIMES IN THERE, THAT THERE ARE
DETAILS THAT ARE NOT GOING TO
LOOK GOOD.
>> YOU MEANT WHY DIDN'T THEY
HAVE IT READY TO GO, A VERSION
FOR THE PUBLIC AND THEN --
>> IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
>> YEAH.
>> I ASKED THAT VERY QUESTION
LAST NIGHT.
GO AHEAD.
SORRY TO INTERRUPT YOU.
>> IT WOULD HAVE MADE FAR LESS
QUESTIONS.
THIS KIND OF DRIBBLING OUT OF
THINGS, IT LOOKS SUSPICIOUS.
IT RAISES QUESTIONS LIKE GARRETT
JUST BROUGHT UP THAT ARE THEY
TRYING TO HIDE SOMETHING?
ARE THEY TRYING TO CONTROL THE
NARRATIVE?
I DON'T KNOW THE ANSWER TO THAT,
BUT IT CERTAINLY RAISES A LOT OF
QUESTIONS HOW THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL IS DOING THIS.
>> HARRY, THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
LAYS OUT IN HIS LETTER THAT
INFORMATION WILL BE REDACTED
FROM THE PORT.
IT INCLUDES TERLT THAT BY LAW
THAT CANNOT BE MADE PUBLIC, THAT
POTENTIALLY COMPROMISES SOURCES
AND METHODS, THAT COULD AFFECT
ONGOING MATTERS AND ANYTHING
THAT WOULD INFRINGE ON THE
PRIVACY OF THIRD PARTIES.
DOES ANYTHING STAND OUT TO YOU
AS SOMETHING TO LOOK FOR IN THAT
LIST?
>> YEAH.
FIRST, I MEAN IT'S A VERY WELL
CRAFTED LETTER.
IT SOUNDS LIKE HE IS BEING
COOPERATIVE, BUT IT IS REALLY
SETTING UP FOR A BATTLE ROYALE.
THE FIRST CATEGORY IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT.
NADLER IS SAYING, WE SHOULD GET
EVERYTHING THAT WAS IN THE GRAND
JURY, BUT WHAT HE IS REALLY
RELYING ON IS PRIOR CASES THAT
GIVE EXTRA AUTHORITY TO THE
COURT.
YOU CAN BET THAT THE DEPARTMENT
OF JUSTICE AND BILL BARR ARE
GOING TO SAY THAT'S NOT UNDER
THE LAW.
UNDER THE LAW, WE JUST HAVE TO
GO WITH THE EXCEPTIONS
DELINEATED IN THIS SPECIFIC
RULE.
NONE OF THEM IS CONGRESS IN AN
IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY.
SORRY, GUYS, BUT THOSE
REDACTIONS ARE GOING TO STAND.
THAT'S THE BIGGEST CATEGORY.
THE LAST CATEGORY STANDS OUT
BECAUSE IT'S NEW AND KIND OF
AMORPHOUS.
WHAT DOES UNDULY MEAN?
WHAT DOES PERIPHERAL MEAN?
THE SECOND AND THIRD CATEGORIES,
I THINK, YOU HAVE TO GIVE HIM
THAT.
NATIONAL SECURITY STUFF,
CERTAINLY THAT MATTERS.
AND ONGOING INVESTIGATIONS,
BUT WHAT'S REALLY GOING TO BE
THE BIG BATTLE IS THIS FIRST
POINT AND NADLER'S GOING TO BE
VERY UPSET, WANT THE DEPARTMENT
TO GO FORWARD AND DO SOMETHING
TOGETHER WITH HIM IN THE COURT.
IT WILL NOT HAPPEN.
>> I WONDER, GARRETT -- SO BARR
SAYS THE SPECIAL COUNSEL MUELLER
IS ASSISTING HIS TEAM IN THIS
REDACTION PROCESS.
I WONDER HOW SIGNIFICANT IS
THAT?
DOES THAT GIVE BARR SOME COVER
HERE?
>> POTENTIALLY.
BUT LET'S REMEMBER SORT OF ONE
BIG OVERARCHING THING.
IT'S NOT LIKE BOB MUELLER DIDN'T
KNOW THAT THESE WERE CONCERNS AS
HE WAS WRITING THIS REPORT.
IT'S NOT THAT, YOU KNOW, HE
TURNED OVER THIS REPORT LAST
FRIDAY AND BILL BARR IS FLIPPING
THROUGH IT, AND HE GOES, OH,
BOB, YOU USED ALL THIS GRAND
JURY TESTIMONY AND INTELLIGENCE
SOURCES AND METHODS.
WE CAN'T RELEASE THIS.
LIKE OBVIOUSLY BOB MUELLER'S
TEAM HAS BEEN THINKING ABOUT
THIS AND WORKING THROUGH THESE
ISSUES FOR MONTHS, IF NOT YEARS.
I MEAN THEY HAVE BEEN THROUGH
THIS PROCESS TO RELEASE
INTELLIGENCE SIGNALS,
INTELLIGENCE INFORMATION IN THE
IRA AND GRU INDICTMENTS.
THERE'S A GOOD PROCESS INSIDE OF
GOVERNMENT TO MAKE THOSE TYPES
OF THINGS PART OF COURT
PROCEEDINGS.
AND WE'VE SEEN IN WATERGATE, AND
WE SAW IN WHITEWATER AND THE KEN
STARR REPORT SORT OF GRAND
JURIES AGREE TO HAND OVER THEIR
INFORMATION TO CONGRESS.
SO THERE IS PROCESS FOR THIS,
AND MUELLER HAS PROBABLY BEEN
THINKING ABOUT HOW TO DO THIS.
AND SORT OF AS MATT WAS SAYING,
IT'S WEIRD TO ME THAT SORT OF
THEY'RE PRETENDING AS IF THESE
ARE BRAND-NEW ISSUES THAT NO ONE
HAD THOUGHT ABOUT PRIOR TO LAST
FRIDAY.
>> MATTHEW, BARR --
>> CAN I --
>> GO FOR IT.
>> THAT'S ABSOLUTELY TRUE, BUT
NOW BARR IS IN CHARGE, AND
MUELLER WILL DEFER ON THE
MATTER.
SO HE MIGHT HAVE THOUGHT IT
WOULD BE RELEASED, BUT BARR IS
GOING TO SAY THAT THAT'S NOT HOW
WE, THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE,
INTERPRET THE RULE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
MORE FROM THE LETTER, MATTHEW.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
ALTHOUGH THE PRESIDENT WOULD
HAVE THE RIGHT TO ASSERT
PRIVILEGE OVER CERTAIN PARTS OF
THE REPORT, HE HAS STATED
PUBLICLY HE INTENDS TO DEFER TO
ME, AND ACCORDINGLY THERE ARE NO
PLANS TO SUBMIT THE REPORT TO
THE WHITE HOUSE FOR A PRIVILEGE
REVIEW.
BUT TONIGHT THE PRENT
TWEETED ON THE REPORT SAYING NO
MATTER WHAT THEY GIVE DEMOCRATS,
IT WILL NEVER BE ENOUGH.
AND MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST TAKE
OUR VICTORY AND SAY NO.
WE'VE GOT A COUNTRY TO RUN.
DO YOU THINK THE PRESIDENT IS
STILL PLANNING TO DEFER TO BARR
HERE?
DOES HE REALLY WANT THE REPORT
OUT?
>> YOU KNOW, I'VE STOPPED TRYING
TO PREDICT WHAT THE PRESIDENT'S
THINKING FROM HIS TWEETS.
IT'S JUST A LOSING GAME.
I DO SUSPECT THERE ARE PEOPLE
AROUND THE PRESIDENT, LIKE I
SAID BEFORE, WHO KNOW THERE ARE
GOING TO BE DETAILS IN THIS
REPORT THAT ARE NOT GOING TO
LOOK GREAT, THAT MAYBE THEY
DIDN'T AMOUNT TO A CRIME.
BUT, YOU KNOW, AS WE'VE DETAILED
IN MANY STORIES OVER THE YEARS
THAT HAVE NOT BEEN CHALLENGED IN
THE LAST TWO YEARS OF CONTACTS,
OF BEING AT THE VERY LEAST
COLLUSION-CURIOUS, AND THAT'S
NOT SOMETHING YOU WANT IN A
PUBLIC SETTING.
WE'RE GOING TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS
HERE.
>> THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME.
HAVE A GOOD WEEKEND.
>>> WE'VE GOT A LOT OF
UNANSWERED QUESTIONS ABOUT THE
MUELLER REPORT, ESPECIALLY WHEN
IT COMES TO THE PRESIDENT'S TIES
TO RUSSIA.
WE'RE GOING TO BREAK DOWN THOSE
QUESTIONS WITH THE FORMER
DIRECTOR OF NATIONAL
INTELLIGENCE, JAMES CLAPPER.'S .
It's not small.
But it's not just big either.
It's the kind of big where
you'll never have to ask,
"Should I scooch up?"
It's big that looks
at a sunroof
and wonders why it can't
just be most of the roof.
It's big that's better
because we built it that way.
The spacious,
121 cubic feet of cargo space
Ford Expedition.
There are a lot of snack bars
out there.
What makes a KIND bar
so special?
Maybe it's the whole nuts
and real fruit.
Maybe it's the drizzle
of dark chocolate.
Maybe it's because
it's tasty and healthy.
Well, there's only
one way to find out.
Do the KIND thing.
♪ ♪
■■,>
Well, there's only
on Cold Lagered...t.
Cold Filtered...
And Cold Packaged,
for Peak Refreshment.
The World's Most Refreshing
Beer. Coors Light.
Okay,
paint a picture fo
And we'd like to puttch
a fire pit out there,
and a dock with a boat, maybe.
Why haven't you
started building?
Well,
Tyler's off to college...
and Mom's getting older...
and eventually we
would like to retire.
Yeah, it's a lot.
But TD Ameritrade can help
you build a plan for today
and tomorrow.
Great.
Can you help us pour
the foundation too?
I think you want a house
near the lake, not in ■■■■■.
■■; a plan.
TD Ameritrade.
♪♪
These folk
The day after chemo
might mean a trip back
to the doctor's office
just for a shot.
But why go back there
when you can stay home
with Neulasta Onpro?
Strong chemo can put you at
risk of serious infection.
In a key study Neulasta
reduced the risk of infection
from 17% to 1%,
a 94% decrease.
Neulasta Onpro is designed
to deliver Neulasta
the day after chemo
and is used by most pa today.
Neulasta is for certain
cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta if you're
allergic to it
or Neupogen (filgrastim).
An incomplete dose could
increase infection risk.
Ruptured spleen,
sometimes fatal as well as
serious lung problems,
allergic reactions,
kidney injuries and capillary
leak syndrome have occurred.
Report abdominal or shoulder
tip pain, trouble breathing
or allergic reactions to
your doctor right away.
In patients with sickle
cell disorders,■
s, sometimes fatal crises
ca
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
If you'd rather be home,
ask your doctor about
with copay card.÷an $5 e
>>> IN HIS LETTER TODAY,
ATTORNEY GENERAL BILL BARR LAID
OUT THE KINDS OF INFORMATION
THAT HE IS WORKING TO REDACT
FROM RELEASING THE MUELLER
REPORT -- BEFORE RELEASING THE
MUELLER REPORT.
HE SAYS SOME OF THOSE REDACTIONS
COULD INCLUDE SENSITIVE
INTELLIGENCE INFORMATION, BUT
ARE CONGRESS AND THE AMERICAN
PUBLIC ENTITLED TO SEE THAT
INFORMATION?
JOINING ME NOW TO DISCUSS IS THE
FORMER DIRECTOR OF NATIONAL
INTELLIGENCE, MR. JAMES CLAPPER.
DIRECTOR, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL SAYS THAT
HE IS IN THE PROCESS OF
IDENTIFYING POTENTIALLY
COMPROMISING, SENSITIVE SOURCES
AND METHODS TO REDACT FROM THE
MUELLER REPORT.
WHAT KIND OF INFORMATION COULD
THAT INCLUDE?
>> WELL, DON, I WOULD TAKE A CUE
FROM THE TWO KEY INDICTMENTS, AT
LEAST FOR ME, THAT MUELLER
ISSUED IN FEBRUARY AND JULY OF
LAST YEAR.
THE ONE IN FEBRUARY WAS THE
INTERNET -- ABOUT THE INTERNET
RESEARCH AGENCY, AND THE ONE IN
JULY WAS ABOUT THE GRU OFFICERS,
THE RUSSIAN MILITARY
INTELLIGENCE ORGANIZATION, AND
INCLUDED INDICTMENTS OF 12 GRU
OFFICERS.
AND I WAS REALLY TAKEN ABACK BY
THE LEVEL OF DETAIL IN THOSE TWO
INDICTMENTS.
A LOT OF FIDELITY, WHICH KIND OF
SURPRISED ME.
NOW, IF THAT'S THE BAR THAT'S
USED, I DON'T THINK -- AND I
THINK THIS IS ONE CASE THAT
CALLS FOR A VERY LIBERAL
INTERPRETATION OF PROTECTING
SOURCES AND METHODS.
AND SO IF THIS REPORT IS 400
PAGES LONG, I WOULD EXPECT AND
HOPE THAT MUCH OF IT IS ABOUT
THE RUSSIAN INTERFERENCE, WHICH
APART FROM THE PRESIDENT'S
CULPABILITY FOR COLLUSION OR
OBSTRUCTION, TO ME, WHAT IS A
HUGE ISSUE HERE, HUGELY
IMPORTANT, IS THE RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE IN OUR POLITICAL
PROCESS, AND IT'S MY GREAT HOPE
THAT THE REDACTION RULES WILL BE
VERY LIGHTLY APPLIED AT LEAST
WHEN IT COMES TO
INTELLIGENCE-RELATED DATA
BECAUSE I THINK THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE ARE ENTITLED TO SEE THAT.
AND IF THOSE TWO INDICTMENTS ARE
AN INDICATOR, THEN I WOULD
EXPECT THIS TO BE A PRETTY
DEVASTATING INDICTMENT OF THE
RUSSIANS, WHICH I THINK IS QUITE
IMPORTANT.
>> INTERESTING.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
COUNTERINTELLIGENCE ASPECT OF
MUELLER'S INVESTIGATION.
BUT NO MENTION OF IT IN BARR'S
LETTER TO CONGRESS OF PRINCIPAL
CONCLUSIONS.
WHERE DO YOU THINK THAT
INVESTIGATION STANDS, DIRECTOR?
>> I HONESTLY DON'T KNOW, AND
THAT, BY THE WAY, IS ANOTHER
REASON WHY I PERSONALLY AM
EXTREMELY INTERESTED IN READING
AS MUCH OF THE MUELLER REPORT AS
WOULD BE MADE AVAILABLE
PUBLICLY, BECAUSE HOPEFULLY IT
WOULD CAST SOME LIGHT ON, FOR
EXAMPLE, THE PRESIDENT'S
INEXPLICABLE DEFERENCE TO
VLADIMIR PUTIN AND WHY -- YOU
KNOW, WHETHER OR NOT THERE IS
POTENTIAL THERE FOR THAT
RELATIONSHIP AND THE DEMEANOR,
THE MANNER OF IT AFFECTING U.S.
POLICY.
AND SO I DON'T ACTUALLY KNOW THE
STATE OF PLAY OF THE
COUNTERINTELLIGENCE
INVESTIGATION AND WHETHER THAT
HAS BEEN SUBSUMED OR WAS
SUBSUMED IN THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION.
I HONESTLY DON'T KNOW.
>> THAT'S WHAT SALARY YATES
PUBLISHED IN HER OP-ED.
>> YES, WHICH I THOUGHT WAS
QUITE GOOD, AND I THINK THERE IS
A COUNTERINTELLIGENCE DIMENSION
HERE.
>> WE WANT TO PUT IT UP.
LET'S PUT IT UP.
WHY WAS THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN
WILLING TO ALLOW THE HELP OF ONE
OF THE COUNTRY'S FOREMOST
GEOPOLITICAL ADVERSARIES RATHER
THAN REPORT THE OVERTURES TO LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
AND AS IMPORTANTLY, DOES THE
ROLE THAT THE RUSSIANS PLAYED IN
HIS ELECTION HAVE ANY BEARING ON
TRUMP'S CURRENT APPROACH TOWARDS
RUSSIA?
>> WELL, EXACTLY.
THAT'S THE POINT.
NOW, THAT WOULD BE AN ARGUMENT
FOR SUSTAINING A
COUNTERINTELLIGENCE
INVESTIGATION.
THAT, AGAIN, IS ANOTHER REASON
WHY THE REVELATION, THE
TRANSPARENCY IS SO IMPORTANT
WITH THE CONGRESS AND WITH THE
PUBLIC, WHETHER IT WILL CAST
LIGHT ON THAT DIMENSION ALONE,
YOU KNOW, THE
COUNTERINTELLIGENCE IMPLICATIONS
AND WHETHER THERE ARE STILL
CONCERNS.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I THOUGHT -- I HAVE TO SAY,
ADAM SCHIFF'S LITANY IN RESPONSE
TO THE REPUBLICAN LETTER
DEMANDING HE RESIGN AS CHAIRMAN
OF THE HOUSE COMMITTEE FOR
INTELLIGENCE, IT'S NOT OKAY, I
THOUGHT WAS A PRETTY COMPELLING
LITANY OF WHY THERE'S SO MUCH
CONCERN ABOUT THE POTENTIAL FOR
COLLUSION.
MAYBE IT DIDN'T REACH THE
EVIDENTIARY BAR FOR CONSPIRACY,
BUT THERE WAS, YOU KNOW, A GREAT
DEAL OF CONCERN AND SUSPICION
ABOUT THAT.
AND THAT WAS EVIDENT AT THE END
OF THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION.
WE DIDN'T UNDERSTAND COMPLETELY
WHAT WAS GOING ON, BUT THERE WAS
A LOT OF CONCERN ABOUT IT.
SO FOR ALL THESE REASONS, IT IS
SO IMPORTANT THAT AS MUCH OF
THIS REPORT AS POSSIBLE BE MADE
PUBLIC.
>> DIRECTOR, THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANKS, DON.
>>> THE HOUSE JUDICIARY CHAIR,
JERRY NADLER SAYS THE APRIL 2nd
DEADLINE FOR THE MUELLER REPORT
STILL STANDS.
WHAT'S NEXT IN THE FACE-OFF
BETWEEN CONGRESS AND THE D.O.J.
I'M GOING TO TALK TO CONGRESSMAN
STEVE COHEN.
THERE HE IS RIGHT THERE.
WE'RE GOING TO DO THAT NEXT.
"Should I scooch up?"
It's big that looks
at a sunroof
and wonders why it can't
just be most of the roof.
It's big that's better
because we built it that way.
The spacious,
121 cubic feet of cargo space
Ford Expedition.
L L L L L
The spacious,
121 cubic feet of cargo space
HOW'D I GET THIS YARD?
BEHIND PETE'S GREAT LOOKING
YARD, IS HIS SECRET WEAPON...
K
THE SCOTTS TURF BUILDER PROGRAM.
IT'S THE BEST WAY TO
GET THE YARD YOU WANT
■■■t■
ALL YEAR LONG, GUARANTEED.
ALL IT TAKES IS 4 FEEDINGS,
WITH A SCOTTS SOLUTION
FOR EVERY SEASON.
AND WITH A CUSTOMIZED PLAN
FROM THE SCOTTS MY LAWN APP,
■CAN LOOK LIKE PETE'
AND WIIT'S THAT EASY. PLAN
FROM THE SCOTTS MY LAWN APP,
THIS IS A SCOTTS YARD.
WNLOAD THE SCOTTS MY LAWN APP
FOR YOUR PERSONALIZED PLAN.
12 hours? 20 dogs?
Where's your belly rubs?
After a day of chasing dogs
you shouldn't have to
cand accept payments
to get paid twice as fast.
(Danny)
It's time to get yours!
(VO)
QUICKBOOKS. BACKING YOU.
■
Check it out, our Unlimited plan
on the brand new
Samsung Galaxy S10.
Oooh.
Premium entertainment on
the infinity screen!
People have seven different
premium entertainment
options to choose from.
'Cause people are different.
Like how you cut the crust
off of your sandwiches,
and I eat them.
And I'm pretty laid
back and casual,
and you... iron your jeans.
I'm actually very happy
you noticed that.
Cool... that's cool.
AT&T has the only unlimited plan
that gives you your choice of
top-tier entertainment.
Buy a new Galaxy S10e,
and get one free.
MORE FOR YOUR THING.
THAT'S OUR THING.
>>> ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR SAYS
IT WILL TAKE UNTIL MID-APRIL TO
COMPLETE REDACTIONS TO ROBERT
MUELLER'S FULL REPORT.
THE HOUSE JUDICIARY CHAIRMAN
JERRY NADLER SAYS THAT'S NOT
GOOD ENOUGH.
LET'S DISCUSS NOW.
CONGRESSMAN STEVE COHEN IS HERE.
HE'S A MEMBER OF THE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE.
THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE YOU JOINING US.
CHAIRMAN NADLER RESPONDED TO
BARR'S LETTER SAYING THAT APRIL
2nd, THAT DEADLINE FOR TURNING
OVER THE REPORT WITHOUT
REDACTIONS, THAT IT STILL
STANDS.
AS A MEMBER OF THE HOUSE
JUDICIARY, HOW DO YOU THINK
DEMOCRATS PROCEED IF BARR MISSES
THAT DEADLINE?
>> WELL, I THINK IT'S GOOD THAT
WE DIDN'T MAKE IT APRIL 1
BECAUSE HE'D HAVE BEEN TRYING TO
MAKE A FOOL OUT OF ALL OF US.
AND I SUSPECT THAT'S WHAT BARR
IS DOING AND TRUMP'S DOING, TO
TRY TO MAKE A FOOL OUT OF
CONGRESS AND A FOOL OUT OF THE
AMERICAN PUBLIC.
THE WHOLE APPOINTMENT, THE
CHARADE OF GETTING THE REPORT
AND ANALYZING IT IS GOING ON, I
THINK THEY WILL NOT HAVE THE
REPORT BY APRIL 2nd.
I SUPPORT CHAIRMAN NADLER.
THE COMMITTEE WILL SUPPORT HIM,
AND I THINK WE'LL PROCEED WITH
THE NEXT ACTION, WHICH I SUSPECT
WILL BE A SUBPOENA.
BUT WE NEED TO BE STRONG AND
FIRM.
WE NEED TO SEE THE ENTIRE
REPORT, AND THE AMERICAN PUBLIC
DESERVES TO SEE THE ENTIRE
REPORT BECAUSE OUR COUNTRY'S
SECURITY VIS-Á-VIS RUSSIA, WHO
WANTS TO BE THE SOVIET UNION
AGAIN, IS SOMEWHAT IN JEOPARDY.
WE'VE GOT A PRESIDENT WHO SEEMS
TO BE SO MUCH IN LOVE WITH KIM
JONG-UN AND VLADIMIR PUTIN THAT
HE CAN'T SEE THE GOODNESS OF HIS
OWN PEOPLE.
>> ONE OF THE KEY ISSUES IN
MAKING MUELLER'S REPORT PUBLIC
IS THE SECRET GRAND JURY
MATERIAL.
NADLER SUGGESTED THAT BARR
SHOULD BE WORKING WITH THE
CONGRESS AND THE COURTS TO GET
THE MATERIAL RELEASED.
WHY ISN'T THAT HAPPENING?
>> BECAUSE THEY DON'T WANT IT
RELEASED.
THEY WANT THE MINIMUM AMOUNT
RELEASED BECAUSE THERE'S SO MUCH
IN THERE THAT WILL BE DAMNING OF
WHAT THIS PRESIDENT HAS DONE AND
TRIED TO DO AND HIS FAMILY AND
OTHERS.
AND THE GRAND JURY TESTIMONY
WOULD BE RELEASED IN OTHER
SPECIAL COUNSEL, INDEPENDENT
COUNSEL CASES.
THE U.S. ATTORNEY GENERAL HAS
WORKED WITH THE COMMITTEES, GONE
TO THE COURTS, AND THE COURTS
HAVE ALLOWED THAT MATERIAL TO BE
GIVEN TO THE CONGRESS.
AND THE COURT CAN DO IT, AND I
FEEL SURE THE FEDERAL DISTRICT
COURT IN WASHINGTON WOULD.
BUT WHEN NADLER ASKED BARR TO
HELP HIM WITH THAT AND TO JOIN
WITH HIM IN MAKING THAT REQUEST,
HE REFUSED BECAUSE HE DOESN'T
WANT IT RELEASED.
IT'S NOT BECAUSE IT'S AGAINST
THE LAW.
HE DOESN'T WANT IT RELEASED, AND
HIS JOB IS TO PROTECT DONALD
TRUMP.
HE IS DONALD TRUMP'S MAN.
>> SO WE DON'T KNOW WHAT'S IN
THERE.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH OR IF
THERE'S ANY DAMNING INFORMATION.
YOU'RE ASSUMING THERE'S DAMNING
INFORMATION, BUT HERE'S MY
QUESTION.
EVERY DAY THAT PASSES, IT ALLOWS
THE PRESIDENT AND HIS ALLIES TO
SUBMIT THE NO COLLUSION
NARRATIVE IN THE PUBLIC
CONSCIOUSNESS.
ARE YOU CONCERNED THAT THE
PUBLIC WON'T BE OPEN TO DETAILS
THAT THE WHOLE REPORT MAY
REVEAL?
>> I THINK A LOT OF THE PUBLIC
WON'T BE, AND I THINK THAT'S
WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
THERE WAS SOMETHING IN A MOVIE,
AND IT WASN'T A GREAT MOVIE OR
ANYTHING ALTHOUGH I LOVED IT
MANY DECADES AGO CALLED "LIBERTY
VALANCE."
THEY SAID WHEN THE LEGEND
BECOMES THE TRUTH, YOU PRINT THE
LEGEND.
AND THEY KNOW THAT.
AS LONG AS THEY CAN MAKE THE
LEGEND THEIR FALSE NARRATIVE,
THE TRUTH, IT WILL BECOME WHAT
IS ACCEPTED AS THE TRUTH.
THEY WANT TO KEEP IT OUT THERE
AS LONG AS POSSIBLE.
THAT'S WHY APRIL 2 IS NOT A GOOD
DATE.
THAT'S WHY HE SAYS POSSIBLY MID
APRIL.
THEN WITH SO MANY REDACTIONS IT
WILL BE LIKE SWISS CHEESE.
THERE'S NOT 400 PAGES OF NO
COLLUSION, NO COLLUSION, NO
COLLUSION.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A LOT OF STUFF
THAT HAS INFORMATION THAT WILL
BE DAMNING TO THE PRESIDENT AND
HIS ADMINISTRATION, AND
OTHERWISE ROBERT MUELLER WOULD
NOT HAVE SAID THIS DOES NOT
EXONERATE THE PRESIDENT.
AND IF THERE'S SOME MATERIAL IN
THERE THAT DOES NOT EXONERATE
HIM, THEY DON'T WANT US TO SEE
IT.
IT'S PROBABLY GRAND JURY
TESTIMONY, OR IT'S EVIDENCE WAS
THE STATEMENT THAT THEY WOULD
NOT RELEASE MATERIAL THAT
WOULD -- INFORMATION THAT COULD
AFFECT THE PERSONAL PRIVACY AND
REPUTATIONAL INTEREST OF
PERIPHERAL THIRD PARTIES.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW WHO THE
PERIPHERAL THIRD PARTIES IS, BUT
I SUSPECT IT'S DONALD TRUMP JR.
AND ERIC AND JAVANKA.
>> YOU THINK THAT'S IT WITH HIS
FAMILY.
WE SHALL SEE AGAIN.
WE DON'T KNOW, BUT A 400-PAGE
LETTER, YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT'S IN
THERE.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW, BUT YOU KNOW
THE AMERICAN PUBLIC DESERVES TO
SEE IT.
WE'VE SEEN THE ENTIRE RESULTS OF
WACO, WHICH WAS THE ONLY THING
UNDER THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
STATUTE IN THE PAST.
THE INDEPENDENT PROSECUTORS,
JAWORSKI AND KEN STARR REPORTS
WERE GIVEN STRAIGHT TO CONGRESS.
THE U.S. ATTORNEYS, THE UNITED
STATES ATTORNEY GENERALS DIDN'T
JUMP IN AND GIVE THEIR
CONCLUSIONS OR OPINIONS TO TRY
TO SET A NARRATIVE AND TO
INTERFERE WITH HOW THE PUBLIC
WOULD INTERPRET IT.
THIS IS VERY UNIQUE.
IT'S VERY DAMAGING.
YOU KNOW WHO BENEFITS FROM THIS?
TWO GROUPS BENEFIT FROM THIS.
DONALD TRUMP AND HIS PEOPLE AND
RUSSIA.
RUSSIA WANTS PEOPLE TO NOT
BELIEVE IN THE UNITED STATES
GOVERNMENT AND DEMOCRACY.
THEY WANT TO DESTROY DEMOCRACY.
THAT'S WHY THEY INTERFERED IN
OUR ELECTIONS.
THAT'S WHY THEY TRIED TO
INTERFERE IN ELECTIONS ALL OVER
EUROPE AND AROUND THE WORLD, IS
BECAUSE THEY DON'T LIKE
DEMOCRACY AND THEY WANT TO
DESTROY IT.
AND ANYTHING THAT HURTS IT HELPS
THE RUSSIANS.
AND THIS HAS HURT DEMOCRACY AND
PEOPLE THINKING THAT THE
GOVERNMENT IS TRANSPARENT, AND
THEY ARE NOT BEING ALLOWED TO
SEE WHAT IS WORK PRODUCT
CONCERNING THEIR PRESIDENT AND
ANY INTEREST HE MIGHT HAVE HAD
WITH RUSSIA AND WHY HE IS SO
SUBORDINATE TO VLADIMIR PUTIN.
>> CONGRESSMAN COHEN, THANK YOU
FOR YOUR TIME, SIR.
>> TAKE CARE, DON.
GOOD TO BE WITH YOU.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>>> HE SERVED HIS TIME, WAS FREE
FOR MORE THAN 12 YEARS, AND WAS
SUDDENLY THREATENED WITH A
RETURN TO PRISON OVER A LEGAL
MIXUP.
NOW DEMET ANDERSON N
TONIGHT.
HE AND HIS ATTORNEY WILL JOIN ME
NUX.
Got a minute?
■■@■
Get Fructis Treats
1 minute hair masks.
The new way
to nourish hair.
98% naturally
derived ingredients.
Use as a creamy mask and
rinse in one minute,
Or leave in for
lasting nourishment.
Get silky hair fast,
with Fructis Treats.
By Garnier,
naturally.
Coors Light is cold filtered.
For brightness and clarity.
with Fructis Treats.
The world's most
refreshing beer.
Coors Light.
Choosing my car insurance was
the easiest decision ever.
I switched to GEICO and
saved hundreds.
That's a win.
But it's not the only
reason I switched.
GEICO's a company I can trust,
with over 75 years of great
savings and service.
♪♪
Now that's a win-win.
Switch to GEICO.
It's a win-win.
Do your asthma symptoms
ever hold you back?■ ■
About 50% of people with
severe asthma
have too many cells called
eosinophils in their lungs.
Eosinophils are a key
cause of severe asthma.
FASENRA is designed to target
and remove these cells.
FASENRA is an add-on
injection for people 12
and up with asthma
driven by eosinophils.
FASENRA is not a rescue
medicine
or for other
eosinophilic conditions.
is proven to help
prevent severe asthma attacks,
imprFASENRA may cause  canor
allections.
■Get help right away if youg of
face, mouth, and tongue, or
trouble breathing.
Don't stop your asthma
treatments
unless your doctor
tells you to.
Tedoctor if you have a
parasitic infection
or your asthma worsens.
Headache and sore throat may
occur.
Haven't you missed enough?
Ask an asthma specialist
about FASENRA.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may
be able to help.
>>> WELL, LAST NIGHT WE TOLD YOU
ABOUT DEMETRIUS ANDERSON.
HE DID HIS TIME.
HE TURNED HIS LIFE AROUND AND
AFTER MORE THAN 12 YEARS OF
FREEDOM, HE WAS THREATENED WITH
A RETURN TO PRISON ALL BECAUSE
OF A LEGAL MIXUP.
WELL, TONIGHT WE HAVE AN UPDATE.
JOINING ME NOW IS DEMETRIUS
ANDERSON AND HIS ATTORNEY,
MICHAEL DOLAN.
ALSO CNN'S VAN JONES.
GENTLEMEN,EVENING.@H FOR JOININ
US.
LET'S GO TO THE ATTORNEY FIRST.
SO YOUAVE SOME NEWS ABOUT
DEMETRIUS' CASE.
CAN YOU SHARE IT WITH US?
>> YES.
I SPOKE TO THE BUREAU OF PRISONS
TODAY, THE COMMUTATION
DEPARTMENT AND THE U.S. ATTORNEY
FROM THE EASTERN DISTRICT OF
PENNSYLVANIA.
THEY BOTH CONFIRMED THAT
DEMETRIUS IS RECEIVING CREDIT
FOR HIS TIME AT LIBERTY, AND
THEREFORE THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT
CONSIDERS HIS 16-MONTH SENTENCE
SERVED.
>> ARE YOU CONFIDENT THAT THIS
IS ALL RESOLVED?
IS THERE A RISK OF THIS, THAT IT
COULD BE CHANGED?
>> LOOK, I'LL FEEL MUCH MORE
COMFORTABLE WHEN I GET THAT IN
WRITING HOPEFULLY ON MONDAY.
BUT THE NEWS I GOT LATE TODAY,
GETTING IT FROM THOSE TWO
SOURCES, I FEEL VERY CONFIDENT
THAT THAT RISK IS GONE.
>> YOU WANT TO SEE IT IN
THE U.S. MARSHAL TO MEET NINE
DAYS AGO, LOST 15 POUNDS, THE
STRESS IS EXTRAORDINARY FOR YOU.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING TONIGHT WITH
THIS INFORMATION?
>> I'M FEELING GRATEFUL,
OVERJOYED, TOTALLY OVERJOYED.
AND FEELING LIKE MY FAITH.
>> YOU SEEM CAUTIOUS THOUGH.
>> I AM BECAUSE I'M CAUTIOUS
ONLY FOR THE FACT THAT I NEED TO
SEE IT IN WRITING.
BECAUSE I'VE SEEN MY RELEASE
PAPERS WRITTEN IN 2006 AND CAME
HOME, SO I WOULD NEED TO SEE
THAT IN WRITING TO FEEL 100%
THAT WHAT I EXPERIENCED LAST
WEEK WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
>> BEN JONES, YOU BROUGHT THE
GIVER REACTION, R.
>> WHEN WE FIGHT, WEWIN.
THIS BROTHER DESERVED EVERYTHING
THAT WAS DONE FOR HIM.
AFTER YOUR SHOW, DON, IT WAS
CRAZY.
I MEAN, SOCIAL MEDIA WENT CRAZY,
CONGRESS PEOPLE WERE CALLING,
PEOPLE SAYING THIS COULD NOT
HAPPEN TO THIS YOUNG MAN.
IT'S TERRIBLE.
HOW COULD YOU HAVE SOMEBODY WHO
DOES WHAT WE SAY DO, MADE A
MISTAKE BUT 13 YEARS, HE'S DONE
PERFECT, DONE PERFECT AND WITH
THIS TSUNAMI OF PUBLIC SUPPORT
FOR THIS YOUNG MAN.
WHEN WE FIGHT, WE WIN.
SO THE FEDERAL DEFENDERS NEED A
ROUND OF APPLAUSE.
THE PROSECUTOR CAME TO THE
TABLE.
THE BUREAU OF PRISON.
I MEAN, IT WAS UNBELIEVABLE WHAT
HAPPENED.
AND LISTEN, WE HAVE TO DO THIS
EVERY TIME WE HEAR ABOUT
INJUSTICE.
WHEN YOU HAVE SOMEBODY WHO'S AN
ASSET FOR THE COMMUNITY, WE'LL
FIGHT TOOTH AND NAIL.
THIS IS A VICTORY TO INSPIRE
PEOPLE ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND IF
THEY COME AFTER SOMEBODY ELSE,
QUIT GOING IN THE DRAWER TRYING
TO FINEOPLE TO PUT BACK
IN PRISON.
LIKE DON'TE ENOUGH PEOPLE
IN ON.
>> ISN'T THIS WHAT'S SUPPOSED TO
HAPPEN WITH THE CRIMINAL JUSTICE
SYSTEM?
IF SOMEONE WITH REST LUGS AND
THEIR DEBT TO SOCIETY, THEY
SHOULD COME OUT AND WORK TO
REFORM THEIR LIVES?
>> DON, I TRUST YOU TO KEEP THE
SPOTLIGHT ON.
I TRUST Dp/p#p/■/TAND
STRONG AND HIS ATTORNEYS TO
STAND WITH HIM AND ALL THE ROOTS
THAT HAVE COME AROUND.
ONCE IT'S ON PAPER, I WANT TO
LOOK AND HOLD UP TO THE LIGHT.
MAKE SURE THERE'S NO INVISIBLE
LEAK ON THERE BUT MOVEMENT WINS.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT PEOPLE TO
UNDERS
WE CAN WALK WITH YOUR HEAD HELD
HIGH.
THIS 48 HOURS OF COMPLETE
TURNAROUND OF THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION CAME TO THE
TABLE, FEDERAL DEFENDERS CAME TO
THu> PREACHERS CAME TO THE
TABLE, PEOPLE CAME TO THE TABLE,
DON, AFTER YOUR SHOW AND MADE A
POSITIVE DIFFERENCE IN SUCH A
SHORT PERIOD OF TIME.
IT WASINGub MEububububub ME ASK.
YOU TRUST, YOU TALK ABOUT THE
PEOPLE YOU TRUST AND THIS
PLATFORM IS ONE OF THEM.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR THAT.
BUT WHAT IS THE BEST WAY TO
PREVENT THIS FROM HAPPENING TO
SOMEONE ELSE?
IS IT AWARENESS?
IS IT LAWS?
WHAT?
>> WELL, LOOK.
I MEAN, OBVIOUSLY, WE'VE GOT TO
CHANGE THE LAWS.
I'M PROUD TO BE THE CEO OF THE
REFORM ALICELIANCE.
DON, YOU'VE BEEN PUTTING THE
SPOTLIGHT ON THIS FOR YEARS AND
YEARS.
PEOPLE KNOW OUR CRIMINAL JUSTICE
SYSTEM HAS GOT TO BE FIXED BUT
DOESN'T BECOME REAL TO PEOPLE
UNTIL THEY SEE A PERSON LIKE
THNG
THROUGH THE SOCK DRAWER, LOOKING
UP FILING CABINETS, HOW TO PUT
MORE PEOPLE IN PRISON.
WE ALREADY HAVE THE BIGGEST
PRISON POPULATION IN THE WORLD,
DON.
WE HAVE MORE PEOPLE IN■■■■■■■■ N
OUR LITTLE COUNTRY THAN CHINA
WITH A BILv■v■ PEOPLE.
FIND GOOD FOLKS TO GIVE THEM A
CHANCE TO COME HOME AND WELLá■R/
u/u/■■■■ A PROOF POINTu#
WHEN WE
WORK ACROSS PARTY LINES,
REPUBLICANS CAME AND DEMOCRATS
CAME.
WHEN WE COME TOGETHER ACROSS
PARTY LINES, WE CAN STOP
INJUSTICE FROM HAPPENING.
IT TAKES PEOPLE LIKE YOU, DON.
YOU WERE THE FIRST ONE TO RUSH
THIS TO THE AIR.
WE APPRECIATE THAT.
BUT THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES.
ALL IT WAS WAS■ THE
TRUTH.
ONCE YOU HEAR THE TRUTH, NOT
GOING TO LET THIS HAPPEN.>> LAS
STILL BELIEVE IN THE JUDICIAL
SYSTEM.
WHAT IS BEHIND THAT BELIEF?
>> MY MOTHER ALWAYS BELIEVED IN
THE JUDICIAL SYSTEM.
ALWAYS TOLD ME TO RESPECT IT.
SO WHEN I DID GET IN TROUBLE, IT
WAS REALLY MORE FOR ME, FOR HER
TO TURN MY LIFE AROUND WHEN I
CAME HOME BECAUSE OF THE PAIN
I'VE SEEN AND I CAUSED HER WHEN
I HAD GOT IN TROUBLE.
I MADE A VOW NOT TO DO IT AGAIN,
FOR HER, AND BY TURNING MY LIFE
AROUND, IT, YOU KNOW, BROUGHT
HER JOY.
BUT WHAT I WENT THROUGH LAST
WEEK WAS JUST RIDICULOUS BECAUSE
WITHIN THE LAST THREE YEARS, I
LOST HER, MY STEPFATHER AND MY
LITTLE SISTER TO THE HANDS OF MY
BROTHER.
WHICH I'M IN THERAPY FOR NOW.
SO WHEN THAT HAPPENED TO ME,
JUST RECENTLY LAST WEEK, WHEN IT
CAME FOR ME AND I KNOW I DIDN'T
EVEN DO ANYTHING WRONG, I DIDN'T
KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I WAS SUICIDAL, COULDN'T EAT.
BECAUSE I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING AND
THEY DIDN'T GIVE ME ANY ANSWER
WHEN IT CAME, YOU KNOW, BUSTING
IN MY HOME LIKE THAT.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE LOOKING FOR
BIN LADEN.
I OPENED MY DOOR, JUST GOT OUT
OF THE SHOWER.
DOING SOMETHING WRONG.
WENT TO THE DOOR, LIKE, I JUST
WANT TO THANK YOU ALSO FOR, YOU
KNOW, HELPING ME, OF COURSE, VAN
JONES, LOUIS REED.
THEY WERE THE ONLY ORGANIZATION
THAT STEPPED UP TO HELP ME, YOU
KNOW, I DON'T KNOW WHAT WOULD
HAVE HAPPENED IF I DIDN'T HAVE
YOU, CNN, YOU KNOW, TO PUT THIS
STORY SO IT WON'T HAPPEN TO
ANYONE ELSE.
>> THAT'S KIND BUT DON'T THANK
ME.
THIS IS WHAT WE ALL SHOULD DO,
ALL OUR BROTHERS' KEEPERS.
THANK YOU.
VAN, THANKS, BROTHER.
>> DON, I TELL YOU WHAT, YOU'RE
A FAIR MAN.
WHEN THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
DOES SOMETHING GOOD, YOU GIVE
HIM CREDIT AND WHEN THEY DO
SOMETHING CREDIT, DON'T GIVE HIM
CREDIT BUT THIS IS ONE TIME THE
PEOPLE AND THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION CAME TOGETHER FOR
JUSTICE AND YOU GAVE US THE
OPPORTUNITY.
>> CAN YOU SAY THAT LOUD FOR THE
PEOPLEp IN THE BACK?
>> MAYBE THE PRESIDENT WAS LIKE
WATCHING, THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION HEARD THE CRIES
OF THE PEOPLE AND HELPED IT
HAPPEN.
YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE YOUR CREDIT,
DON, GIVING IT TO YOU.
>> THANK Y ALL, I APPRECIATE
IT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
Your mammoth masterpiece.
And...whatever this was.
Because we make our meat
with the good of the deli and
no artificial preservatives.
Make every sandwich count
with Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh.
After months of wearing
only a tiger costume,
we're finally going on the
trip I've been promising.
Because with Expedia,
I saved when I added
a hotel to our flight.
♪
So even when she outgrows
her costume,
'll never outgrow the memory
of our adventure together.
Unlock savings when
you add select hotels
to your existing trip.
Only when you book
with Expedia.
♪♪
Be right back.
With moderate
to severe Crohn's disease,
I was there, just not
always where I needed to be.
Is she alright?
I hope so.
So I talked to my doctor
about HUMIRA.
I learned HUMIRA is for people
who still have symptoms
of Crohn's disease
after trying other medications.
And the majority
of people on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom relief
and many achieved remission
in as little as 4 weeks.
■■■■
l■&■&ability
■d infections,
s■■■■■
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, ■g■vkg,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Ñ■
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Be there for you, and them.
Ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA,
remission is possible.
I have a vision
correction number,
But I'm more than a number.
When I'm not sharing ideas
with my colleagues
I'm defending my kingdom.
My Essilor lenses offer more
than vision correction
with three innovative
technologies
For my ultimate in vision
Clarity
And Protection