THERE'S NO MIDDLE GROUND ON THIS
ONE.
>> ALSO JUST A QUICK REMINDER,
THE PRESIDENT CAN'T AUTHORIZE
SPENDING.
A BUDGET PROPOSAL IS DEAD ON
ARRIVAL AND ASPIRATIONAL.
THAT'S WHAT THE APPROPRIATIONS
COMMITTEE DID, SO HE DIDN'T SAY
OKAY ON THE SPENDING, HE JUST
CHANGED HIS MIND ON THE BUDGET
DETAIL.
>>> THANKS FOR JOINING US ON
"INSIDE POLITICS."
WE'LL SEE YOU BACK HERE SUNDAY
AT8:00 A.M.
BRIANNA KEILAR STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>>> I'M BRIANNA KEILAR LIVE FROM
CNN'S WASHINGTON HEADQUARTERS.
IT IS FRIDAY, IT IS NEARLY
APRIL, AND THE MUELLER REPORT IS
STILL A SECRET.
BUT PRESIDENT TRUMP GIVING US A
bb OF ■T/gN■■;■■#■#■/■POST-MUEL
FIGHTING MOOD HE'LL BRING TO THE
20 CAM WITH A■ F■ AGGRESSIVE
AND EVEN PROFANE ATTACK ON■  FI7
NOT JUST THE FOUR-PAGE SUMMARY
WITH VERY SMALL QUOTES FROM THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL.
OUR KAITLAN COLLINS IS AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
WHAT ARE WE HEARING FROM THE
PRESIDENT, KAITLAN?
>> Reporter: IT WAS■F■F■F■F■F■F
THE 2016 CAMPAIG ENDED, BUT HE
DIDN'T JUST VINDICATE HIMSELF IN
THE RUSSIA INVESTIGATION, HE
ALSO SAID IT WAS ONE FOR HIS
SUPPORTERS AS WELL, ANDRAMED
THE PEOPLE INVESTIGATING THE
PRESIDENT IN HIS CAMPAIGN■■■■ W
APART THE COUNTRY.
THE PRESIDENT DIDN'T SAVE■■■■■■
TOUGHEST LANGUAGE FOR THEM BUT
ALSO FOR D■■■WELL.
THE PRESIDENT SEEMED TO DELIGHT
THIS TAKING A VICTORY LAP AROUND
THEM.
>> AFTER THREE YEARS OF LIES AND
SMEARS AND SLANDER, THE RUSSIA
HOAX IS FINALLY DEAD.
TOTAL EXONERATION, COMPLETE
VINDICATION.
THE DEMOCRATS HAVE TO NOW DECIDE
WHETHER THEY WILL CONTINUE
DEFRAUDING THE PUBLIC WITH
RIDICULOUS [ BLEEP ].
ROBERT MUELLER WAS A GOD TO THE
DEMOCRATS.
THEY DON'T LIKE HIM SO MUCH
RIGHT NOW.
>> Reporter: NOW, HE DIDN'T JUS
REFERENCE DEMOCRATS GENERALLY.
HE WENT AFTER THE CHAIRMAN OF
THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE, ADAM SCHIFF
SPECIFICALLY, SEVERAL TIMES
MOCKING HIM THROUGHOUT THE
NIGHT.HEARD THIDENT THERE
SOME■F, AND IT REALLY
ILLUMINATED THE ANGER HE FELT
THERE IN THE FIRST 20 MINUTES OR
SO OF THAT SPEECH.
BUT THEN THE PRESIDENT WENT ON
AND STARTED SPEAKING, AND IT
STARTED TO SOUND LIKE HIS PAST
RALLIES AND MADE PEOPLE AT THE
WHITE HOUSE I SPOKE TO WONDER IF
THE PRESIDENT IS GOING TO MISS
HAVING THIS FIGHT OF THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION.
>> WE'LL E.
KAITLAN COLLINS, THANK YOU SO
MUCH AT THE WHITE HOUSE FOR US.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS RAILING
RIGHT NOW ON IMMIGRATION,
THREATENING TO SHUT DOWN THE
SOUTHERN BORDER.
IN A SERIES OF TWEETS, THE
PRESIDENT SAYS IF MEXICO DOESN'T
IMMEDIATELY STOP ALL ILLEGAL
IMMIGRATION COMING INTO THE
UNITED STATES THROUGH OUR
SOUTHERN BORDER, I WILL BE
CLOSING THE BORDER OR LARGE
SECTIONS OF THE BORDER NEXT
WEEK.
OUR ED LAVENDARA IS JOINING ME
ON THE PHONE.
ED, THIS IS A PRETTY DIRE THREAT
FROM THE PRESIDENT.
TELL ME WHAT CLOSING THE BORDER
WOULD DO WHERE YOU ARE?
>> Reporter: IS HE TALKING ABOUT
ESSENTIALLY TALKING ABOUT
CLOSING EVERY BRIDGE, EVERY PORT
OF ENTRY, NOT ALLOWING ANY
COMMERCE OR TRUCKS TO COME BACK
AND FORTH THROUGH THE BORDER,
NOT TO MENTION THE MILLIONS OF
PEOPLE WHO CROSS THE BORDER
EVERY DAY AS PART OF EVERYDAY
LIFE ON THE SOUTHERN BORDER?
THE DETAILS OF EXACTLY HOW THIS
WOULD PLAY OUT WOULD DICTATE A
LOT OF HOW THIS WOULD LOOK.
BUT OVERALL, THE IDEA OF CLOSING
DOWN THE BORDER, I'T
OV■pJUST HOWHOCKING■■■■TULD BE
IN THE BORDER RN IN THE
SOUTHERN UNITED STATES, AND WHAT
THAT WOULD MEAN ECONOMICALLY,
NOT JUST FOR THE SOUTHERN BORDER
REGIONS, BUT FOR THE REST OF THE
COUNTRY.
IT'S HARD TO OVERSTATE, AGAIN,
JUST WHAT KIND OF IMPACT THAT
WOULD HAVE ON THE U.S. ECONOMY
WHEN YOU THINK OF THE TENS■■S■
THOUSANDS OF TRUCKS THAT MOVE
GOODS AND SERVICES BACK AND
FORTH ACROSS THE BORDER FROM
BROWNSVILLE, TEXAS ALL THE WAY
TO SAN DIEGO, CALIFORNIA.
THAT WOULD BE A SHOCKING AND
STUNNING DEVELOPMENT TO HAPPEN
ALONG THE U.S. SOUTHERN BORDER.
>> INDEED.
ED LAVENDARA, THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR THAT, TALKING TO US FROM
BROWNSVILLE, TEXAS.
PRESIDENT DONALD TRUMP SAID HE
PUT TOGETHER A GROUP OF FOUR OR
FIVE SENATE REPUBLICANS TO COME
UP WITH A VIABLE ALTERNATIVE TO
OBAMACARE.
WE HAVE JEREMY DIAMOND JOINING
US WITH THE DETAILS.
IS THIS THE CASE, JEREMY?
>> IT CERTAINLY DOESN'T APPEAR
TO BE AT THIS POINT, BRIANNA.
WE KNOW THE PRESIDENT TALKED
YESTERDAY ABOUT FOUR OR FIVE
REPUBLICAN SENATORS HE WAS
PUTTING TOGETHER TO TRY AND
ADVANCE THIS ISSUE, TRY AND GET
SOME KIND OF REPLACEMENT FOR
OBAMACARE IF INDEED THIS RULING
STRIKING DOWN THE ENTIRETY OF
THE HEALTH CARE LAW IS INDEED
UPHELD.
BUT WE SPOKE WITH SEVERAL
SOURCES ON CAPITOL HILL AND THE
WHITE HOUSE, AND IT DOES NOT
APPEAR SUCH A WORKING GROUP DOES
EXIST IN SUCH FORM OR FASHION.
THE NAMES WE CHECKED BEHIND THIS
SAID THEIR OFFICE DIDN'T MENTION
THE EXISTENCE OF ANY KIND OF
WORKING GROUP.
WHAT THEY SAID WAS THOSE
SENATORS, BILL CASSIDY, RICK
SCOTT, FOR EXAMPLE, JOHN VERASO,
THEY ARE INDEED CONTINUING TO
HAVE CONVERSATIONS ABOUT HEALTH
CARE WITH THE PRESIDENT AND WITH
THEIR COLLEAGUES.
ONE REPUBLICAN SENATOR TOLD ME
SPECIFICALLY THAT IT APPEARS
THAT THE PRESIDENT WAS SIMPLY
TALKING ABOUT INDIVIDUALS HE HAS
TALKED TO ABOUT HEALTH CARE.
BUT AS FAR AS THE EXISTENCE OF
AN ACTUAL WORKING GROUP TO COME
UP WITH A REPLACEMENT, IT
DOESN'T APPEAR THAT THAT IS THE
CASE.
AND THAT IS WHERE WE FIND THIS
ADMINISTRATION, PUSHING THIS
POSITION TO FULLY INVALIDATE
OBAMACARE THROUGH THE COURTS
WITHOUT ACTUALLY HAVING ANY KIND
OF A REPLACEMENT READY TO GO.
BRIANNA?
>> JEREMY DIAMOND, THANK YOU FOR
THAT FACT CHECK THERE.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS NOW
TAKING CREDIT FOR SAVING THE
SPECIAL OLYMPICS FROM A CRISIS
THAT WAS CREATED BY HIS OWN
ADMINISTRATION.
EDUCATION SECRETARY BETSY DeVOS
HAS BEEN SQUARING E ING OFF WIT
CONGRESS ON HER BUDGET W
CALLS FOR LIMITING FUNDS FOR
SPECIAL OLYMPICS.
HERE ARE PEOPLE QUESTIONING THE
DECISION?
>> ARE YOU QUESTIONING THE
DECISION OF THE EDUCATION
SECRETARY TO REMOVE SPECIAL
OLYMPICS FUNDING?
>> THAT IS ONE OF THE MORE ODD
MOMENTS I HAVE SEEN.
BUT AS THE PRESSURE MOUNTED
TOWARD DeVOS, THE PRESIDENT
STEPPED IN.
>> I HAVE BEEN TO THE SPECIAL
OLYMPICS.
I THINK IT'S INCREDIBLE.
I JUST AUTHORIZED A FUNDING.
I HEARD ABOUT IT THIS MORNING.
I HAVE OVERRIDDEN MY PEOPLE.
WE ARE FUNDING THE SPECIAL
OLYMPICS.
>> A.B.'S DAUGHTER IS HERE.
THIS HAS BEEN A WATER COOLER
KIND OF THING IN D.C. HERE ALL
WEEK.
WE SHOULD POINT THAT OUT.
HE ALSO SAYS HE THINKS THE
SPECIAL OLYMPICS ARE INCREDIBLE.
HE DOESN'T HAVE SUCH A GOOD
TRACK RECORD WHEN HE TALKED
ABOUT ESPECIALLY THE
PARALYMPICS.
HE SAID THEY WERE HARD TO WATCH.
SO HE LIKES TO COME IN AND BEING
THE SAVIOR WHILE SIMULTANEOUSLY
THROWING BETSY DeVOS UNDER THE
BUS OR ALLOWING HER TO SOMEHOW
CHANGE HER MIND ON THIS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> WE SHOULD ALSO POINT OUT,
BRIANNA, HE DIDN'T AUTHORIZE ANY
FUNDING YESTERDAY FOR SPECIAL
OLYMPICS.
THE CONGRESS AUTHORIZE SPS
SPENDING.
IN THE PROPOSED BUDGET, THEY
PROPOSED MAKING SOME CUTS IN
THIS PROGRAM.
THEY WOULD HAVE TO WRITE IT INTO
THE FUNDING BILL, WHICH THEY
DIDN'T.
SO THE FACT HE TOLD US THAT HE
OVERRODE HIS PEOPLE AND
AUTHORIZED FUNDING IS ALSO
FACTUALLY INCORRECT.
REX TILLERSON, HIS FORMER
SECRETARY OF STATE, HAD TO BE
CALLED OUT ON TWITTER FOR ALL
THE WORLD TO SEE ON INNORTH KORN
POLICY.
VICE PRESIDENT PENCE HAS HAD TO
EXPERIENCE THIS.
MAKING IT CLEAR THAT HE IS THE
FINAL DECIDER.
IT'S NOT A TEAM EFFORT OVER
THERE.
IT WAS PAINFUL TO SEE BETSY
DeVOS' REACTION AFTER THE
PRESIDENT SAID HE OVERRODE THIS
BECAUSE SHE WAS TRYING TO
INDICATE SHE HAD BEEN FOR FULL
FUNDING OF THIS ALL ALONG.
THIS IS THE COST OF WORKING IN
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION, NO
QUESTION, AND I WAS FASCINATED
TO SEE THAT THE SMALL BUSINESS
ADMINISTRATION SECRETARY IS
PLANNING TO STEP DOWN AND GO
BACK TO THE PRIVATE SECTOR.
PEOPLE KNOW THAT THIS IS A
SHORT-TERM AND FRUSTRATING
EXPERIENCE AND THAT'S WHY THERE
IS SO MUCH TURNOVER IN THIS
WHITE HOUSE.
>> ARE WE GOING BACK TO JEREMY
DIAMOND AT THE WHITE HOUSE?
LET'S GO BACK TO JEREMY DIAMOND
AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
JEREMY, YOU HAVE SOME NEWS.
TELL US.
>> WE CAN NOW CONFIRM WITH A
SOURCE FAMILIAR WITH HER PLANS
THAT OLIVIA McMANN, HEAD OF THE
SMALL BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION,
DOES PLAN TO LEAVE HER POSITION.
SHE DOES PLAN TO RESIGN.
WE'RE TOLD THAT RESIGNATION,
THAT ANNOUNCEMENT, COULD COME AS
EARLY AS TODAY.
THAT IS JUST COMING THROUGH
RIGHT NOW, BRIANNA.
AS YOU KNOW, SHE IS ONE OF THE
FEW WOMEN IN THE PRESIDENT'S
CABINET.
SHE'S ALSO ONE OF THE WEALTHIEST
MEMBERS OF THE PRESIDENT'S
CABINET.
SHE WAS A FORMER WWE EXECUTIVE,
IF YOU'LL REMEMBER.
WE WERE TOLD SHE WAS GUNNING FOR
A MORE SENIOR ROLE, AND THAT
WOULD BE COMMERCE SECRETARY.
BUT AS OF NOW IT APPEARS SHE'S
RUNNING THE ADMINISTRATION, BUT
IT'S NOT CLEAR WHY EXACTLY THAT
IS OR WHAT IS PUSHING THIS
DECISION.
BUT THAT IS WHAT WE'RE LEARNING
AT THIS HOUR, BRIANNA.
>> WE WERE JUST DISCUSSING THIS.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN FOR THE
ADMINISTRATION, THAT LINDA
McMANN IS LEAVING?
>> IT'S VERY INTERESTING SHE
MIGHT HAVE BEEN INTERESTED IN
BECOMING COMMERCE SECRETARY.
WILBUR ROSS HAS BEEN FACING
QUESTIONS ABOUT HIS STOCK TRADES
AND NUMEROUS THINGS, SO THERE
WAS A TIME WHEN PEOPLE THOUGHT
HE WAS ALSO MAYBE GOING TO BE
SUMMARILY SHOOED OUT OR ASKED TO
RESIGN.
I THINK SHE DECIDED TO LEAVE,
THAT IT WAS TIME TO GO.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH BACKLASH
SHE HAS FACED IN HER POSITION.
HE CERTAINLY HASN'T BEEN
RESPECTFUL TO HER IN PUBLIC AS
HE HAS JAMES MATTIS AND A LOT OF
OTHER PEOPLE.
AS I SAID, THIS IS A VOLATILE
PLACE TO WORK.
WE SEE TURNOVER LIKE WE HAVE
NEVER SEEN IN AN EXECUTIVE
BRANCH IN THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION BEFORE.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP MOCKING
ASYLUM ERS, CLAIMING MANY OF
THEM ARE PROTESTING AS THERESA
MAY'S BREXIT DEAL FAILS AGAIN.
>>> SOMELY FINDINGS FROM
INVESTIGATORS IN THE CRASH OF
THE SECOND JET.
Choosing my car insurance was
the easiest decision ever.
I switched to GEICO and
saved hundreds.
That's a win.
But it's not the only
reason I switched.
GEICO's a company I can trust,
with over 75 years of great
savings and service.
♪♪
Now that's a win-win.
Switch to GEICO.
It's a win-win.
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
■■■■W■■■■ñ■
from any one else.
Why accept it
from your allergy pills?
Flonase relieves
your worst symptoms
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
Flonase helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances.
Most pills only block one.
Flonase.
If your moderate to
severe ulcerative colitis
or Crohn's symptoms
are holding you back,
and your current treatment
hasn't worked well enough
it may be time for a change.
Ask your doctor about ENTYVIO®,
the only biologic
developed and approved
just for UC and Crohn's.
ENTYVIO® works at the site of
inflammation in the GI tract,
and is clinically
proven to help many
patients achieve both
symptom relief and remission.
Infusion and serious allergic
reactions can happen
during or after ■■
ENTYVIO® may
increase risk of infection,
which can be serious.
PML, a rare, serio
potefatal brain
infection caused by  virus.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infectio■tt
experience frequent infections
or have flu-like
symptoms, or sores.
Liver problems can
occur with ENTYVIO®.■
If your UC or Crohn's
treatment isn't working for you,
ask your gastroeist
about ENTYVIO®.
ENTYVIO®.
Relief and Remission
within reach.
>>> SO AS WE REPORTED EARLIER,
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS THREATENING
TO SHUT DOWN THE SOUTHERN
BORDER.
HERE'S THE TWEET.
IF MEXICO DOESN'T IMMEDIATELY
STOP ALL ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION
COMING INTO THE UNITED STATES AT
OUR SOUTHERN BORDER, I WILL BE
CLOSING THE BORDER OR LARGE
SECTIONS OF THE BORDER NEXT
WEEK.
THESE ARE COMMENTS THAT COME AS
THE PRESIDENT MOCKED ASYLUM
SEEKERS IN MICHIGAN LAST NIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW THEY'RE ALL MET BY
THE LAWYERS.
THEY COME OUT, THEY'RE ALL MET
BY THE LAWYERS, AND THEY SAY,
SAY THE FOLLOWING PHRASE, I AM
VERY AFRAID FOR MY LIFE.
I AM AFRAID FOR MY LIFE.
OKAY, AND THEN I LOOK AT THE
GUY, HE LOOKS LIKE HE JUST GOT
OUT OF THE RING, HE'S A
HEAVYWEIGHT CHAMPION OF THE
WORLD.
IT'S A BIG FAT CON JOB, FOLKS.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE ACTUALLY ARE
FAMILIES.
THAT'S REALLY THE TREND THAT
WE'RE SEEING.
WE HAVE ROBERT PEREZ, THE DEPUTY
COMMISSIONER IN CUSTOMS FOR
BORDER PROTECTION TO TALK ABOUT
THE STATE OF THINGS ON THE
BORDER.
THERE IS THIS THREAT TO SHUT
DOWN PARTS OF THE BORDER.
WHAT WOULD THAT MEAN FOR THE
CUSTOMS AND BORDER PATROL, BUT
ALSO THE PRESIDENT IS CLEARLY
TRYING TO PRESSURE MEXICO.
WHAT IS THE CBP LOOKING FOR FOR
SUPPORT FROM THE OTHER SIDE OF
THE BORDER?
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME,
BRIANNA.
A PLEASURE TO BE WITH YOU.
LOOK, WE ARE BEYOND THE BREAKING
POINT.
WE HAVE REACHED AN UNPRECEDENTED
LEVEL WITH RESPECT TO THIS
CRISIS SITUATION, THE AMOUNT OF
UNDOCUMENTED MIGRANTS THAT ARE
ARRIVING ALONG OUR SOUTHERN
BORDER.
WE HIT AN HISTORIC HIGH LAST
MONTH WITH 67,000.
WE PROJECT WE WILL REACH 100,000
THIS MONTH.
AND IT'S NOT JUST THE BORDER
PATROL FRON THE FRONT LINE, BUT
THE ENTIRE IMMIGRATION WAS NEVER
DESIGNED TO DEAL WITH THESE
TYPES OF NUMBERS, AND THE
DEMOGRAPHICS, WHICH IS REALLY
IMPORTANT TO UNDERSTAND, IF I
COULD SHARE WITH YOU, THE
MAJORITY OF PEOPLE THAT ARE
COMING ARE FAMILY UNITS.
MORE THAN HALF ARE FAMILY
UNITS --
>> 65%, RIGHT?
>> 65%, EXACTLY, BRIANNA.
IT HAS CLOGGED THE ENTIRE
SYSTEM, OVERWHELMED IT.
WE'RE AT A POINT WHERE OUR FRONT
LINE MEN AND WOMEN ARE DOING AN
EXCEPTIONAL JOB OVER AND ABOVE
THE CALL OF DUTY IN DEALING WITH
THIS UNPRECEDENTED CRISIS, BUT
OUR FACILITIES, OUR LEGAL
FRAMEWORK, OUR RESOURCING, OUR
INFRASTRUCTURE, TECHNOLOGY,
CAPACITY WAS NEVER DESIGNED OR
BUILT FOR THIS.
SO, YES, LOOK, WE NEED TO WORK
WITH OUR MEXICAN COUNTERPARTS.
THIS IS A REGIONAL ISSUE AND WE
ALL NEED TO MAKE SURE WE'RE
DOING EVERYTHING WE POSSIBLY CAN
TO DEAL WITH THIS CRISIS.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN IF PARTS
OF THE BORDER ARE TOTALLY SHUT
DOWN?
WHAT DOES THAT LOOK LIKE?
>> WHAT THAT LOOKS LIKE IS A
PRETTY SEVERE CONSEQUENCE WITH
RESPECT TO NOT ONLY THE ECONOMIC
FLOWS.
WE WELCOME ITS CUSTOMS AND
BORDER PROTECTION AT OUR POINTS
OF ENTRY.
NEARLY 400 MILLION TRAVELERS A
YEAR, $2 BILLION WORTH OF TRADE.
NEARLY 3 MILLION TRUCKS, CARGO
CONTAINERS EVERY YEAR.
THERE IS A SEVERE IMPACT, AND
WHAT'S IMPORTANT TO UNDERSTAND
IS THAT THE CRISIS IS SO SEVERE
RIGHT NOW, WE ARE LITERALLY
TRYING TO SAVE LIVES.
WE ARE FOCUSED ON SAVING THE
LIVES OF CHILDREN IN PARTICULAR
WHO ARE BEING TRAFFICKED, WHO
ARE BEING TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF BY
CRIMINAL HUMAN SMUGGLING
ORGANIZATIONS AND GIVEN PROMISES
ALONG WITH THESE VERY VULNERABLE
POPULATIONS AND BEING BROUGHT
INTO CONDITIONS THAT ARE FRANKLY
JUST TOTALLY, TOTALLY
INADEQUATE.
>> YOUR COMMISSIONER GAVE A BIG
SPEECH IN EL PASO THIS WEEK, AND
HE SAYS ONLY ABOUT 10 OR 15% OF
THE ASYLUM CLAIMS ARE CREDIBLE.
THE ASYLUM GRANT RATE IS 25%,
AND EVEN THAT DOESN'T REFLECT
THE VIABILITY RATE.
THERE ARE QUESTIONS OF HOW
PEOPLE SEEKING ASYLUM, WHAT THEY
WOULD GET.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THOUSANDS,
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE WHO
MEET THIS BORDER REQUIREMENT.
WHAT IS BORDER PROTECTION DOING
TO PROTECT THOSE PEOPLE?
>> WE ARE JUST IN THE FRONT END
PART OF THAT PROCESS.
THESE HUMAN SMUGGLING AND
CRIMINAL ORGANIZATIONS, BY
VIRTUE OF TAKING ADVANTAGE OF
THESE VULNERABLE POPULATIONS AND
SATURATING THE ENTIRETY OF THE
SYSTEM WELL BEYOND BORDER AND
PROTECTION VIOLATION, BY THE
TIME THEY GET IN FRONT OF A
JUDGE AND THEY FIND THEIR CLAIMS
NOT TO BE CREDIBLE MAKES THOSE
INDIVIDUAL ASYLUM SEEKERS LOST,
IF YOU WILL, AND BEHIND SO MANY
OF THESE OTHER CLAIMS THAT ARE
BEING MADE.
SO WHAT WE'RE TRYING TO DO IS
GETTING TO THOSE LEGITIMATE
ASYLUM SEEKERS --
>> THERE ARE LEGITIMATE ASYLUM
SEEKERS THAT ARE NOT REPRESENTED
IN THAT NUMBER.
I KNOW THE STATS SAY 20.
THERE ARE LEGITIMATE ASYLUM
SEEKERS NOT REPRESENTED IN THAT.
THERE IS A QUESTION RIGHT NOW OF
THERE MAY BE LEGITIMATE ASYLUM
SEEKERS, THERE MAY BE NOT ENOUGH
CAPACITY -- AND WE'RE SEEING
THAT.
WE SEE PEOPLE THAT MAY HAVE A
LEGITIMATE CLAIM BUT THEY'RE
BEING DENIED.
>> I WOULD RESPECTFULLY SUGGEST
THEY ARE NOT BEING DENIED.
WHAT IS HAPPENING IS THAT,
AGAIN, THE SYSTEM IS ABSOLUTELY
SATURATED WITH MANY MORE FOLKS
WHO, IN THE END OF THEIR ASYLUM
PROCESS, WOULD BE FOUND NOT TO
HAVE A VALID CLAIM, AND WE'RE
DOING OUR BEST TO GET THOSE
PEOPLE AT THE FRONT OF THE LINE
AND GIVE THEM AN OPPORTUNITY TO
ACTUALLY MAKE THEIR LEGITIMATE
CLAIMS.
BUT NEVERTHELESS, AGAIN --
>> SO WHAT DO YOU NEED, THEN?
LONG TERM, SHORT TERM?
YOU HAVE PEOPLE IN EL PASO IN AN
UNDERPASS FENCED IN WITH BARBED
WIRE.
AND I'M WONDERING IF YOU'RE
ABLE, CVP, TO PROVIDE WHAT IS
UNDER THE LAW TO BE PROVIDED FOR
THEM.
WHAT DO YOU NEED IN THE SHORT
TERM AND ALSO WHAT DO YOU NEED
IN THE LONG TERM?
BECAUSE THIS PROBLEM ISN'T GOING
AWAY AND IT'S BEING FUELED BY
VIOLENCE IN CENTRAL AMERICA.
>> SO WHAT WE NEED IS A
COMPREHENSIVE AND REALLY A
FULL-BLOWN PACKAGE OF RESOURCING
BY WAY OF INFRASTRUCTURE,
PHYSICAL INFRASTRUCTURE,
TECHNOLOGY, PERSONNEL ALONG THE
BORDER TO BE ABLE TO DEAL WITH
THE CRIMINAL FLOWS, THE DRUG
FLOWS, THE NATIONAL SECURITY
CONCERNS, AND ON THE
HUMANITARIAN SIDE AS WELL, WE
NEED THE LEGAL FRAMEWORK TO BE
FIXED.
WE NEED CONGRESS TO ACT.
I MYSELF HAVE TESTIFIED UP ON
CAPITOL HILL.
WE'VE BEEN RINGING THIS BELL FOR
MONTHS, IF NOT YEARS, NOW ABOUT
CONGRESS' NEED TO FIX THE LEGAL
FRAMEWORK, TO KEEP FAMILIES
TOGETHER THROUGH THE ENTIRETY OF
THEIR ASYLUM CLAIMS AND ALSO BE
ABLE TO RETURN, UNACCOMPANIED
MINORS.
THESE ARE THE GROUPS AND
POPULATIONS, BRIANNA, THAT ARE
BEING TAKEN ADVANTAGE OF AND
THEY'RE BEING BROUGHT UP AND
SMUGGLED BY THESE CRIMINAL
ORGANIZATIONS.
THEY ARE BEING PUT IN A SYSTEM
THAT IS ABSOLUTELY OVERWHELMED.
SO IT'S A LEGAL ISSUE AND A
LEGAL FRAMEWORK THAT WE NEED
CONGRESS TO FIX FOR ALL OF US.
>> CAN YOU SAY THAT CBD CAN
PROVIDE WHAT IS NEEDED FOR THOSE
FOLKS WHO ARE UNDER A BRIDGE IN
EL PASO?
BECAUSE THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO HAVE
SHELTER, FOOD AND WATER,
ADEQUATE MEDICAL CARE?
CAN YOU COMMIT THAT YOUR
ORGANIZATION IS PROVIDING THAT?
>> I CAN NOT ONLY COMMIT BUT I
CAN ALSO ASSURE YOU THAT, AS A
PARENT MYSELF, AND OUR AGENTS
AND OFFICERS WHO ARE MANY OF
THEM PARENTS THEMSELVES, ARE
DOING EVERYTHING THEY ABSOLUTELY
CAN TO SAVE CHILDREN'S LIVES AND
SAVE THE LIVES AND PROTECT THE
WELL-BEING OF ALL THESE
INCREDIBLY VULNERABLE
POPULATIONS WE'RE ENCOUNTERING.
OVER AND ABOVE THE CALL OF DUTY
FOR THE LARGEST LAW ENFORCEMENT
AGENCY IN THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT.
>> ALL RIGHT, THERE HAVE BEEN
SOME CHALLENGES.
WE HAVE TO WRAP IT UP THERE.
THERE HAVE BEEN SOME CHALLENGES
WITH THAT AND THAT MAY BE AN
UNDERSTATEMENT.
ROBERT PEREZ,HANK YOU FOR
T/s AND TALKING
WITH US.
>>> WE HAVE SOM MORE■O CLUES IN
THE CRASH THAT KILLED EVERYONE
ON THE PLANE.
>>> AND THE COURT BLOCKS ANOTHER
TRUMP ATTEMPT TO UNDERMINE
OBAMACARE.
that begins with nature.
To treat every car
like I treat mine.
♪♪
At ADP we're designing
a better way to work,
so you can achieve
what you're working for.
♪♪
Here is another Laundry Hack
from Home Made Simple.
Do you want ready to wear
clothing without all the hassle?
You can, with Bounce Dryer
sheets.
Simply toss two sheets in the
dryer to iron less.
We dried one shirt without
Bounce,
and an identical shirt using
Bounce.
The Bounce shirt has fewer
wrinkles, less static,
and more softness and
freshness.
For extra large or wrinkly
loads, toss in three sheets.
Dermatologist tested Bounce Free
and Gentle
is free of dyes and perfumes.
Bounce out wrinkles, Bounce out
static.
From the start, the C-Class
was ahead of its time.
Still, we never stopped
making it stronger.?÷
Faster.
m■■>8/■nxnxnxn■Qú÷■÷
Because to be the best,
is to never ever stop
making it better.
The new 2019 C-Class Family.
Visit your local■■■
Mercedes-Benz dealer for
exceptional lease &
financing offers during
the Mercedes-Benz Spring
Event. Going on now.
♪♪
■■■
Be right back.
With moderate
to severe Crohn's disease,
I was there, just not
always where I needed to be.
Is she alright?
I hope so.
So I talked to my doctor
about HUMIRA.
I learned HUMIRA is for people
who still have symptoms
of Crohn's disease
after trying other medications.
And the majority
of people on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom relief
and many achieved remission
■
in as little as 4 we
HUMIRA c■■■■T/%&
saw significant symptom relief
and &d infections,remission
■■
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lympve
ede blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
x your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Be there for you, and them.
Ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA,
remission is possible.
You're turning onto the
street
when you barely
clip a passing car.
Minor accident
—no big deal, right?
Wrong. Your insurance
company is gonna raise
your rate after the other
car got a scratch so small
you coulda fixed
it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that
pen and use it to sign up
with a different
insurance company.
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because of
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>>> TODAY A MAJOR NEW CLUE IN
THE ETHIOPIAN AIRLINES FLIGHT
THAT KILLED 157 PEOPLE WHEN IT
CRASHED.
THE "WALL STREET JOURNAL" IS
REPORTING THAT INVESTIGATORS
HAVE REACHED A PRELIMINARY
CONCLUSION THAT A STALL
PREVENTION SYSTEM ON THAT BOEING
737 MAX 8 ACTIVATED AUMATICALL
AIR LAST737 MAX 8LANES ARE
GROUNDEDFORE HERE WITH
RETTYIGNI AND
WHATLSE, TOM?HA WE'VE B
ING AND WHAT WE'VE BN OVER
HERE HAD THE SAME HALLMARKS AS
THATNTHS YEARLIER
BASICALLY WHAT MCAS DOES,
PIE  STWARE THAT
TDO,OUAV A BAD THE
TH P UP, IT M Y TO IT DN, MAKIN.
THEN AS THE CREW TTHE P AND THE
COMPES TO PUSH
NOW IT IS SUGEDHA IN PROBABLY AS
BOEING, AFR THE AIR CRAS SOFTWAR
WE'RE GOIOT STOPS H THE SKY,
BUT THEYEUT AN
INDICATO COCKPIT TO LET
IF THE SSORSON'TGR ABOUTE  THEN
IT WON'TURN AND IT
MAKE IT LIT EASIER TOIGHTCK AND
ANE AHUTDOWN. BOEI, THOUGH,
IS THIS IS N J AECHNIC NOTH TO
MUCH FOR
NOW, THE PRESINT WANTS TO
KILLOBAMACKI W A
REAN.LEMS NO SUCH WORKING  EXIS.
>>> PLU
LINOISROSECURS
DIS JUSSIE  CAS ALAFFRO
PROSECUTORS THE  PRE ON THE
SENATOR IISASE TO RESIGN?
My digestive system used
to make me feel sluggish
But now, I take
Metamucil every day.
It traps and removes the
waste that weighs me down,
So I feel lighter.
Try Metamucil, and begin to
feel what lighter feels like.
You're turning onto the
street
when you barely
clip a passing car.
Minor accident
—no big deal, right?
Wrong. Your insurance
company is gonna raise
your rate after the other
car got a scratch so small
you ulda fixed
it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that
pen and use it to sign up
with a different
insurance company.
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because of
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
Ok everyone!
Our mission is to provide
complete, balanced nutrition...
For strength and energy!
Whoo-hoo!
Great-tasting Ensure.
With 9 grams of protein
and 26 vitamins and minerals.
Ensure, for strength and energy.
Look for savings in
your weekly paper.
>>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A PLAN
THAT IS SO MUCH BETTER THAN
OBAMACARE.
THE HEALTH CARE IS GOING VERY
WELL.
YOU CAN ALWAYS TAKE CARE OF
PREEXISTING CONDITIONS, JUST
REMEMBER THAT.
ALWAYS PREEXISTING CONDITIONS.
BUT OBAMACARE IS TOO COSTLY FOR
PEOPLE, THEY CAN'T AFFORD IT AND
THE DEDUCTIBLE, WHICH AVERAGES
MORE THAN $7,000, MEANING UNLESS
SOMEBODY HAS GOT REALLY BIG
PROBLEMS, CAN'T EVEN USE IT.
OBAMACARE IS A DISASTER.
RIGHT NOW IT'S LOSING IN COURT.
RIGHT NOW IN THE TEXAS COURT, AS
YOU KNOW, PROBABLY ENDS UP IN
THE SUPREME COURT, BUT WE'RE
DOING SOMETHING THAT IS GOING TO
BE MUCH LESS EXPENSIVE THAN
OBAMACARE FOR THE PEOPLE.
I'M NOT SAYING GOVERNMENT, I'M
SAYING FOR THE PEOPLE.
AND WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
PREEXISTING CONDITIONS AND WE'LL
HAVE A MUCH LOWER DEDUCTIBLE.
AND I'VE BEEN SAYING IT, THE
REPUBLICANS ARE GOING UP
BEING THE PARTY OF HEALTH CARE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> THE PRESIDENT THERE IN
FLORIDA WITH SOME DUBIOUS FACTS
ALSO ABOUT OBAMACARE.
THE PRESIDENT ONCE AGAIN
CLAIMING THAT A HEALTH CARE PLAN
IS COMING AS HE ASKS THE COURTS
TO END OBAMACARE.
KEEP IN MIND A FEDERAL JUDGE HAS
JUST BLOCKED ANOTHER ATTEMPT BY
THE ADMINISTRATION TO UNDERMINE
OBAMACARE.
THEY WANT TO OFFER ALTERNATIVES
TO HEALTH CARE EXCHANGES.
WE HAVE BETTY LUJAN WITH US.
YOU JUST PROPOSED A WIDE-RANGING
LL WITH TWEAKS TO OBAMACARE.
TELL US YOUR REACTION TO THE
PRESIDENT SAYING THERE IS NO
GREAT URGENCY IN CING UP WITH
A NEW HEALTH CARE PLAN.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME, AND
IN TERMS OF WHERE I'M COMING
FROM IN MY PART OF SOUTHEASTERN
PENNSYLVANIA, ABOUT 300,000 OF
US IN MY COMMUNITY WOULD END UP
WITHOUT HEALTH CARE IF
PREEXISTING CONDITIONS WEREN'T
COVERED.
AND FROM DAY TO DAY, HOUR TO
HOUR, IN FACT, WITH OUR
PRESIDENT, I'M NOT CERTAIN WHERE
HE LANDS ON PREEXISTING
CONDITION AND UNDERMINING THE
AFFORDABLE CARE ACT, AND WHAT
ENDS UP HAPPENING IS A
COMMUNITY, MY COMMUNITY, IS
WORRIED ABOUT WHETHER THEY WILL
HAVE AFFORDABLE QUALITY,
ACCESSIBLE HEALTH CARE, AND THE
INDUSTRY ALSO ASSOCIATED WITH IT
IS WORRIED ABOUT WHETHER THE
STABILIZATION WILL HAPPEN OR NOT
HAPPEN.
I THINK HE'S CREATING AN
ENORMOUS AMOUNT OF UNCERTAINTY
WHICH ENDS WITH A LOT OF PEOPLE
BEING WORRIED.
>> YOU JUST HEARD HIM TALK ABOUT
PREEXISTING CONDITIONS.
THEY'RE SAYING IT'S ALWAYS GOING
TO BE COVERED.
WE DO HEAR THIS CONSISTENTLY
FROM REPUBLICANS AND FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE, BUT DO YOU BELIEVE
IT?
>> I FRANKLY DON'T, BECAUSE I
FEEL AS THOUGH PRETTY MUCH EVERY
OTHER DAY WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
BLOWING UP THE AFFORDABLE CARE
ACT WHICH IS, IN FACT, A VEHICLE
WE HAVE RIGHT NOW IN THE NATION
THAT IS PROTECTING PEOPLE WITH
PREEXISTING CONDITIONS, AND SO I
THINK THAT THIS IS A STEM
ALBEIT FLAWED THAT DEFINITELY
NEEDS TWEAKING, AS YOU
MENTIONED.
THAT IS THE SYSTEM OF OUR NATION
RIGHT NOW.
AND IF WE SHOULD BE WORKING AT
THIS, WE SHOULD B WORKING TO
FIX THE AFFORDABLE CARE ACT
RATHER THAN BLOWING IT UP AND
STARTING ALL OVER AGAIN.
>> IF THE ADMINISTRATION
SUCCEEDS IN DOING THAT, IN
BLOWING THIS UP, SCRAPPING
OBAMACARE ENTIRELY, WHAT WOULD
IT TAKE FOR A DEMOCRATIC HOUSE,
A REPUBLICAN SENATE AND THIS
PRESIDENT TO FIND A HEALTH CARE
LAW THAT THEY COULD AGREE ON?
IS THAT EVEN POSSIBLE?
>> SO, YOU KNOW, I COME FROM A
VERY PURPLE PART OF OUR COUNTRY.
WE ARE VERY PRAGMATIC PEOPLE.
I AM COMPLETELY WILLING TO WORK
WITH THE ADMINISTRATION AND WITH
THE REPUBLICAN-CONTROLLED
CONGRESS AND THE DEMOCRATICALLY
CONTROLLED HOUSE.
BECAUSE IT REALLY IS THAT
IMPORTANT THAT WE FIX THE
ACCESSIBILITY AND AFFORDABILITY
OF QUALITY HEALTH CARE FOR OUR
PEOPLE.
BUT I'M DUBIOUS, PROBABLY AT
BEST, IN TERMS OF THE
OPPORTUNITY THAT THIS
ADMINISTRATION PROVIDES FOR THAT
PATHWAY.
>> SO I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT THE PRESIDENT'S RALLY LAST
NIGHT.
THE PRESIDENT'S SON DONALD JR.
WAS WARMING UP THE CROWD, AND HE
DID SO BY BLASTING YOUR FELLOW
FRESHMAN CONGRESSWOMAN
ALEXANDRIA OCACIO-CORTEZ.
THE CROWD RESPONDED BY SAYING
"AOC SUCKS."
LET'S WATCH.
>> WHAT IS IT ABOUT HER, YOUR
COLLEAGUE IN THIS INCOMING CLASS
THAT MAKES HER SUCH A LIGHTNING
ROD FOR CONSERVATIVES, DO YOU
THINK?
>> I GUESS WHAT I WOULD SAY IS
THERE WERE TWO THINGS THAT WERE
REALLY SIGNATURE ISSUES IN MY
CAMPAIGN AND IN MANY CAMPAIGNS
ACROSS THE COUNTRY THAT WERE
IMPORTANT TO PEOPLE.
ONE WAS HEALTH CARE.
THE SECOND THING WAS CIVILITY
AND DECENCY.
WE'VE SEEN THESE TWO THINGS COME
UP IN THIS CONVERSATION RIGHT
NOW, WHICH IS IT'S ABSOLUTELY
UNACCEPTABLE THAT WE ARE
MALIGNING PEOPLE WHO DON'T AGREE
WITH OUR BELIEFS.
I THINK WE SAW IT WITH SENATOR
McCAIN, THE WAY TO BEHAVE WHEN
WE'RE IN THINGS LIKE TOWN HALLS,
IN THINGS LIKE RALLIES AND
PEOPLE ARE MALIGNING AND
DISPARAGING PEOPLE NOT LIKE US.
AND THAT'S NOT OKAY.
WE EXPECT MORE FROM OUR
LEADERSHIP OF ALL FORMS IN TERMS
OF THE WAY THAT WE MODEL BEING A
DECENT REPRESENTATIVE OF OUR
COMMUNITY.
SO I'M DISAPPOINTED IN PRESIDENT
TRUMP AND IN PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
SON, FRANKLY, IN NOT LEADING BY
EXAMPLE IN THIS PARTICULAR CASE.
WE CAN AGREE TO DISAGREE, BUT WE
SHOULDN'T DISRESPECT EACH OTHER.
>>CONGRESSWOMAN, THANK YOU SO
MUCH.
CONGRESSWOMAN CHRISSY HOULAHAN
JOINING US.
>>> A BREXIT VOTE ENDS IN A
PIV
PIVOTAL DECISION OF WHAT BECOMES
DOOMS DAS DAY.
>>> WATCH "TRICKY DICK" RIGHT
HERE ON CNN SUNDAY AT 9:00 P.M.S
That's a win.
But it's not the only
reason I switched.
GEICO's a company I can trust,
with over 75 years of great
savings and service.
♪♪
Now that's a win-win.
Switch to GEICO.
It's a win-win.
My mom washes the dishes...
...before she puts them in the
dishwasher.
So what does the dishwasher do?
Cascade Platinum does the work
for you,
prewashing and removing
stuck-on foods,
the first time.
Wow, that's clean!
Cascade Platinum.
Opening doors with Cologua
Turning 50 opens the
door to a lot of new things...
like now your doctor may be
talking to you
Turabout screeninghe
door tofor colon cancer.ngs...
Luckily there's me,
Cologuard.
The noninvasive test
you use at home.
It all starts when your
doctor orders me.
Then it's as easy
as Get, Go, Gone.
You get me when I'm
delivered...
right to your front door
and in the privacy of your
own home.
There's no prep or
special diet needed.
You just go to the bathroom,
to collect your sample.
After that, I'm gone,
shipped to the lab for
DNA testing
that finds colon cancer
and precancer.
Cologuard is not right for
everyone.
It is not for high risk
individuals,
including those with a history
of colon cancer or precancer.
IBD, certain hereditary
cancer syndromes,
or a family history
of colon cancer.
Maybe I'll be at
your door soon!
Ask your doctor if
Cologuard is right for you.
Covered by Medicare
and most major insurers.
>>> THE BRITISH GOVERNMENT
PLANNED FOR THIS TO BE A
HISTORIC DAY, BREXIT DAY.
PARTIES WERE PLANNED, COINS WERE
MINTED FOR THIS OCCASION, AS YOU
CAN SEE HERE.
IT'S STILL HISTORIC BUT NOT FOR
THE REASONS THEY HAD HOPED.
>> THE AYES TO THE RIGHT, 286.
THE NOS TO THE LEFT, 344.
>> MR. SPEAKER, I THINK IT
SHOULD BE A MATTER OF PROFOUND
REGRET TO EVERY MEMBER OF THIS
HOUSE THAT ONCE AGAIN WE HAVE
BEEN UNABLE TO SUPPORT LEAVING
THE EUROPEAN UNION IN AN ORDERLY
FASHION.
>> THERE HAS TO BE AN
ALTERNATIVE PLAN.
THE PRIME MINISTER MUST GO NOT
AT ANY DETERMINED DATE IN THE
FUTURE BUT NOW SO WE CAN DECIDE
THE FUTURE OF THIS COUNTRY
THROUGH A GENERAL ELECTION.
>> SO ANOTHER PLAN VOTED DOWN.
A PRIME MINISTER ON THE BRINK OF
RESIGNING AND ALMOST THREE YEARS
OF PLANNING TO LEAVE THE
EUROPEAN UNION ON HOLD.
RICHARD QUEST OF "QUEST MEANS
BUSINESS" IS OUTSIDE OF
PARLIAMENT.
RICHARD, THERE ARE SO MANY
QUESTIONS HERE.
THE BIG ONE IS, WHAT HAPPENS
NEXT?
>> Reporter: IF I KNEW THAT
NOBODY KNOWS.
ANYONE WHO DOES SAY THEY KNOW IS
LYING.
PARLIAMENT HAS NOW SINGULARLY
REFUSED TO PASS THE PRIME
MINISTER'S DEAL THREE TIMES.
AND SO NOW EUROPE HAS SAID,
WELL, YOU CAN HAVE HER LONGER IF
YOU WANT IT, BUT YOU NEED TO
COME UP WITH WHAT YOU WANT.
THERE WILL BE MORE VOTES NEXT W.
PARLIAMENT HAS TAKEN OVER,
BASICALLY, AND THEY'RE DOING THE
VOTES THEMSELVES.
THERE ARE SOME REALLY CRUEL
ANALOGIES BEING DRAWN, BRIANNA.
FOR EXAMPLE, THE ■4MONTI■PYTHON
SKETCHES OF WHICH EVERYONE IS SO
FAMILIAR.
THEY'RE DESCRIBING THE PRIME
MINISTER'S DEAL AS THE DEAD
PARROT.
NO, SHE'S JUST RESTING.
AND THESE PROTESTERS ESSENTIALLY
SAYING, GET ON WITH IT.
IT IS BY NO MEANS CERTAIN THE
U.K. WILL LEAVE THE EUROPEAN
UNION, BUT IT IS ABSOLUTELY 100%
WITHOUT ANY SHADOW OF DOUBT A
TOTAL UTTER MESS.
>> WHAT HAPPENS WITH THE PRIME
MINISTER?
IS SHE GOING TO STAY OR GO,
RICHARD?
>> IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF WHEN.
SHE PROMISED TO GO IN A DEAL
WASN'T PASSED.
IT WASN'T PASS■/■/■/
ARE JUST WONDERING WHEN SHE'S
GOING TO GO.
IT'S SIMPLY NOT LIKELY THAT
SHE'LL BE THE PRIME MINISTER AT
THE END OF THE YEAR.
THE ONLY THING THAT'S KEEPING
HER THERE IS SHEER FEAR BY MANY
MPs OF WHAT WILL COME NEXT AND
THEN PAY A MEMBER OF PARLIAMENT
WHO IS FURTHER RIGHT WING AND
MORE HARD LINE BREXIT.
THE PM IS BASICALLY DEAD WOMAN
WALKING.
>> ALL RIGHT, RICHARD QUEST IN
LONDON, THANK YOU.
>>> A NEW TWIST IN THE JUSSIE
SMOLLETT SCANDAL AS THE CITY OF
CHICAGO DEMANDS HE PAY UP.
THE-FIGURE TAB HE'S BE
The most awarded SUV ever.
At Fidelity, we help you
prepare for the unexpected
with retirement planning and
advice for what you need today
and tomorrow.
Because when you're
with Fidelity,
there's nothing to stop you
from moving forward.
Are you an ocean?
Because when you're
with Fidelity,
No.
Are you edible?
♪♪
Can't sleep.
Me neither.
Woo!
Number one!
♪♪
AHHHH!
[laughter]
♪♪
We're here.
♪♪■>■á■>
Hi I'm Joan Lunden.
Today's senior living
communities have never
been better,
with amazing amenities like
movie theaters, exercise rooms
and swimming pools, public
cafes, bars and bistros
even pet care services.
and there's never been
an easier way to get great
advice.
A Place for Mom is a
free service
that pairs you with a local
advisor
to help you sort through
your options
and find a perfect place.
A Place for Mom.
You know your family
We know senior living.
Together we'll make the right
choice.
.
>>> PROSECUTORS WHO DROPPED
FELONY CHARGES AGAINST ACTOR
JUSSIE SMOLLETT HAVE
FUNDAMENTALLY MISLED THE PUBLIC
ON THE LAW AND THE DISMISSAL OF
THE CHARGES.
THAT IS THE ACCUSATION FROM AN
ILLINOIS LAWYERS GROUP ABOUT
COOK COUNTY STATE'S ATTORNEY KIM
FOX AND HER OFFICE AND HOW
THEY'VE HANDLED THIS.
A GRAND JURY HAD INDICTED
SMOLLETT ON 16 COUNTS IN A HATE
CRIME HOAX AND IN A STUNNING
REVERSAL THE PROSECUTOR DROPPED
THE CHARGES AGAINST SMOLLETT ON
TUESDAY SPARKING OUTRAGE FROM
THE PRESIDENT, ILLINOIS
LAWMAKERS, CHICAGOANS INCLUDING
THE MAYOR OF CHICAGO WHO SAID
THAT HE WANTS SMOLLETT TO PAY
MORE THAN $130,000 TO COVER THE
COST OF THE INVESTIGATION.
LET'S BRING IN ERIC SUSSMAN.
HE'S A FORMER FIRST ASSISTANT
STATE ATTORNEY FOR KIM FOX.
HE'S JOINING US FROM CHICAGO.
WITH YOUR PERSPECTIVE OF HAVING
WORKED IN THIS OFFICE WITH KIM
FOX, DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT
HAPPENED HERE?
>> WELL, I MEAN, THE BEST I CAN
TELL, BOTH FROM WORKING IN THE
OFFICE AS WELL AS TALKING TO THE
LAWYERS ON BOTH SIDES, IS THAT
THE DEFENSE LAWYERS FOR JUSSIE
SMOLLETT WENT IN AND THEY TOLD
THE PROSECUTORS THEY HAVE
SERIOUS PROBLEMS WITH THEIR
CASE.
I DON'T KNOW IF SOME OF IT HAD
TO DO WITH THE REASONS WHY THE
STATE'S ATTORNEY RECUSED HERSELF
AND THE PROSECUTORS ULTIMATELY
AGREED TO DISMISS THE CHARGES
AND THEN ONCE THE PUBLIC GOT
UPSET AND OUTRAGED, THEY TRIED
TO JUSTIFY IT BY CALLING IT
EITHER A DEFERRED PROSECUTION OR
SAYING THIS HAPPENS ALL THE
TIME, BOTH OF WHICH ARE
DEMONSTRATIVELY FALSE.
I THINK THOSE ARE THE DECEPTIONS
THAT THE ILLINOIS STATE
PROSECUTORS ASSOCIATION IS
ZEROED IN ON AND THE FACT THAT,
REALLY, AT THIS POINT THEIR
MISLEADING THE PUBLIC IN TERMS
OF WHAT REALLY HAPPENED HERE.
>> FOX SAYS AND HER OFFICE SAYS
THAT SEALING THIS CRIMINAL
CASE -- EVERYONE WANTS TO KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED BECAUSE IT WAS
SEALED AND THEY'RE SAYING IT WAS
MANDATORY, THIS LAWYERS GROUP
SAYS THAT IS NOT TRUE.
DO YOU THINK IT WAS MANDATORY?
>> IT IS NOT MANDATORY.
THAT IS FALSE.
AND THE STATE'S ATTORNEYS OFFICE
THERE WAS A MOTION -- AN ORAL
MOTION THAT WAS MADE.
THE STATE'S ATTORNEY'S OFFICE
DIDN'T OBJECT.
THEY SHOULD HAVE OBJECTED.
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS, THERE
WAS NO CONVICTION TO EXPUNG, SO
IT IS COMPLETELY SHROUDED IN
MYSTERY AS TO WHY THE JUDGE
ULTIMATELY SEALED THESE RECORDS.
THERE CLEARLY WAS NO MANDATORY
REASON WHY THEY SHOULD HAVE BEEN
SEALED AND QUITE FRANKLY,
THERE'S NO LEGAL REASON WHY THEY
SHOULD BE SEALED AT THIS POINT
IN TIME.
>> THERE WAS ALSO AMONG THESE
CONTRADICTIONS THIS EXAMPLE OF
WHETHER FOX FORMALLY RECUSED
HERSELF BECAUSE SHE DIDN'T.
SHE MADE IT SOUND LIKE SHE WAS
RECUSING HERSELF BUT HAD SHE
RECUSED HERSELF HER OFFICE
LIKELY WOULD NOT HAVE HANDLED
THIS CASE.
SHOULD SHE HAVE PROPERLY AND
FULLY RECUSED HERSELF IN THE
LEGAL SENSE OF THE WORD?
>> THERE ARE TWO ISSUES HERE.
THE FIRST QUESTION IS, DID THE
STATE'S ATTORNEY HAVE A CONFLICT
OF INTEREST?
BASED ON WHAT WE HAVE SEEN IN
TERMS OF THE DISCUSSIONS WITH
TINA CHEM AND THE DSSIO
WITH THE VICTIM'S FAMILYR
WITNESSES FAMILY THAT'S NOT A
BASIS TO ASSUME THERE'S ANY TYPE
OF CONFLICT OF INTEREST.
THERE HAS TO BE A CONFLICT THERE
FOR THE PROSECUTOR TO EVEN THINK
OF RECUSING HERSELF.
TO BE CLEAR,STATE'S ATTOR
INTERVIEW WITNESSES, MEET WITH
FALY MEMBERS, MEET WITH
DEFENDANTS ALLHE TIME.
THERE'S AN ENTIR UNIT OF THE
STATE'S ATTORNEYS OFFICE AND
THAT'S ALL THEY DO.
THERE'S NOTHING BASED ON WHAT
WE'VE SEEN IN THE RECORD THAT
WOULD EXPLAIN WHY THE STATE'S
ATTORNEY BELIEVED SHE NEEDED TO
RECUSE HERSELF ANY WAY, SHAPE OR
FORM.
THEN WE GET TO THE SOND
ISSUE -- SORRY.
>> OH, NO.
I ONLY HAVE A MINUTE WITH YOU, I
HAVE A QUESTION I REALLY WANT
ANSWERED.
IT'S A BROADER QUESTION.
SO THIS WHOLE THING IS A MESS BY
MANY ACCOUNTS.
IT'S BEEN MISHANDLED, MS. FOXX
HAS OTHER IMPORTANT CASES SHE'S
HANDLING.
SHE ENCOURAGED R. KELLY ACCUSERS
TO COME FORWARD AND THEY IT.
DOES SHE HAVE GOOD JUDGMENT TO
HANDLE THESE OTHER THINGS?
>> WELL, I MEAN, THE ANSWER IS
CLEARLY SHE HAS SHOWN POOR
JUDGMENT IN THIS CASE IN TERMS
OF THE STATEMENTS SHE'S MAKING
ABOUT MR. SMOLLETT AFTER THE
CHARGES HAVE BE DROPPED WHICH
ARE CLEARLY A VIOLATION OF
PROSECUTORIAL ETHICS RULES AND
E SECOND THING IS, I HAVE
NEVER IN MY LIFE, AND I CAN'T
THINK OF A PROSECUTOR THAT WOULD
EVER GET ON AND MAKE A PUBLIC
STATEMENT SOLICITING INFORMATION
TO TRY TO PROSECUTE SOMEONE LIKE
R. KELLY.
IT'S IMPROPER.
R. KELLY IS A PRIVA CITIZEN.
HE'S PRESUMED INNOCENT AND UNTIL
THEY BRING CHARGES, THERE IS NO
BASIS FOR THEM TO BE OUT THERE
IN ESSENCE FISHING FOR
INFORMATION AND THEN GETTING