MANEUVER INTO SOME SORT OF TALKS
THAT WOULD BE THE BEST POSITION
FOR THEM.
>> OKAY.
KIM BER LE, THANK YOU FOR THE
EXPERTISE.
APPRECIATE IT.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
IT IS THE TOP OF THE HOUR.
GOOD MONDAY MORNING.
I'M IN NEW YORK.
WE BEGIN WITH THIS HOUR FEDERAL
PROSECUTORS HAVE JUST UNSEALED
AN INDICTMENT AGAINST JEFFREY EP
TEEN.
INSIDE IT THE ALARMING DETAILS
OF HOW THE POLITICALLY CONNECTED
BILLIONAIRE ALLEGEDLY RAN A SEX
TRAFFICKING RING.
HE'S ACCUSED OF SEEKING OUT
MINERS AND PAYING CASH TO GIRLS
AS YOUNG AS 14 YEARS OLD AND
THEN PAYING THEM TO RECRUIT
OTHER GIRLS FOR HIM TO ABU
ANUND IN PUBLIC.CHARGES WILL BE
A PRESS CONFERENCE WILL BE HELD
WITH PROSECUTORS AND THE FBI AND
LATER THIS MORNING EPSTEIN WILL
APPEAR IN COURT.
STILL UNKNOWN WHAT THIS CASE
COULD REVEAL ABOUT HIS POLITICAL
CONNTIS, AND THEY INCLUDE A
BRITISH ROYAL, A
PRESIDENT AND THE CURRENT ONE,
EPSTEIN, QUOTE, A TERRIFIC GUY.
WE HAVE TEAM COVERAGE THIS
MORNING.
OUR ANCHOR AND NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT ERICA HILL IS
ME
COURTHOUSE.
SHIMON, Y HELDRE
ND ADEY ENCOUNT
ESCALATED.
AND SOME OF THE GIRLS SAYING --
IN SOME OF JULIE BROWN'S
REPORTING, WE SHOULD POINT OUT.
THE ALLEGED VICTIMS TALKING
ABOUT HOW THEY DIDN'T KNOW IT
WAS GOING TO MAYBE GO THAT WAY.
OR THEY KNEW IT WASN'T RIGHT,
BUT AGAIN, THEY WERE YOUNG AND
DIDN'T GET IT.
AND IT ALSO POINTS OUT IN THE
INDICTMENT THAT THEY BELIEVE,
PROSECUTORS BELIEVE HE DID KNOW
THEIR AGES AND WHAT WAS GOING
ON, BECAUSE SOME OF THESE
VICTIMS WHO WERE IN HERE WERE
ASKED SPECIFICALLY ABOUT THEIR
AGE AND THEY SAID THEY DIDN'T
LIE.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THE POWERFUL
PEOPLE IN POLITICS THAT WERE
FRIENDS, INCLUDING PRESIDENT
BILL CLINTON, WHICH I THINK
RECORDS SHOW FLEW ON HIS JET
SEVERAL TIMES.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS QUOTED WITH
GLOWING WORDS ABOUT HIM BACK IN
2002.
>> NAIN FACT.
IN 2002 HE TALKED ABOUT HIM TO
NEW YORK MAGAZINE, HE SAID HE'S
A TERRIFIC GUY, HE'S A LOT OF
FUN TO BE WITH.
IT'S EVEN SAID THAT HE LIKES
BEAUTIFUL WOMEN AS MUCH AS I DO,
AND MANY OF THEM ARE ON THE
YOUNGER SIDE.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT, JEFFREY
ENJOYS HIS SOCIAL LIGHT.
OBVIOUSLY THAT'S SEEN IN A FAR
DIFFERENT LIGHT TODAY.
BUT THERE IS A CONNECTION HERE.
YOU MENTIONED FORMER PRESIDENT
CLINTON FLYING ON HIS PLANE,
BEING ON HIS PRIVATE ISLAND.
PRESIDENT TRUMP REPORTEDLY ON
HIS PLANE.
AND AT ONE POINT EP TEEN WAS A
MEMBER OF MAR-A-LAGO AND HAD
BEEN THERE BUT WAS BARRED AT ONE
POINT.
HE WAS ACCUSED OF SEXUALLY
ASSAULTING AN UNDERAGE GIRL
THERE.
>> I WOULD BE REMISS NOT TO
BRING UP WITH YOU, THE CURRENT
LABOR SECRETARY ALEXANDER ACOSTA
WHO IS VERY TIED TO THIS BECAUSE
HE WAS A PART OF SECURING THE
SWEET PLEA DEAL FOR EPSTEIN BACK
IN 2008 THAT GOT HIM VERY LITTLE
JAIL TIME, CHARGED WITH
PROSTITUTION, NOT SEX
TRAFFICKING, AND, BY THE WAY,
THAT NONE OF THE VICTIMS KNEW
ABOUT.
>> NO.
THEY DIDN'T.
SO A COUPLE OF POINTS THERE.
NUMBER ONE, YOU'RE RIGHT.
ALEXANDER ACOSTA AT THE TIME WAS
THE U.S. ATTORNEY FOR THE
SOUTHERN DISTRICT SO HE HAD TO
OVERSEE THIS DEAL.
HE TO SAY OKAY WITH TEAM OF
ATTORNEYS.
AT THE TIME HE SAID THEY LACKED
THE EVIDENCE TO PROVE THAT HE
HAD VIOLATED FEDERAL LIEU.
THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF PUSHBACK
ON THAT SINCE.
WELL, THE DOJ IS INVESTIGATING
HOW THE CASE WAS HANDLE.
WE SHOULD ALSO POINT OUT THAT IN
FEBRUARY A FEDERAL JUDGE SAID
THIS DEAL BROKE THE LAW BECAUSE
THE VICTIMS DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT
IT.
THE TERMS OF THIS DEAL, WHICH
IT'S BEEN SAID MULTIPLE TIMES
WERE BASICALLY DICTATED BY
EPSTEIN'S ATTORNEYS, POWERFUL
ATTORNEYS, THEY DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT IT.
THE DEAL WAS KEPT QUIET AND KEPT
APART FROM THE VICTIMS UNTIL A
JUDGE SIGNED OFF ON IT.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
THAT BROKE THE LAW.
>> GREAT REPORTING.
OBVIOUSLY WE'LL BE ON THIS ALL
DAY BECAUSE HE'S GOING TO BE IN
COURTHIS MORNING.
LET'S TALK ABOUT WHERE THIS
GO■■■RMER FEDERAL PROSECUTOR IS
HERE.ARE A G VOICE■;■;■;
THIS BECAUSE YOUE ACTUALLY
PROSECUTED SEX TRAFFICKING CASES
BEFORE.
ONE THING THAT SHIMON SAID
OUTSIDHEOURTENTS
AGO THAT STRUCK ME, IS THAT WHAT
MAY BE DIFFERENT THIS TIME THAN
THE PLEA DEAL IN 2008 IF THIS
GOES TO ■TRIAL, IS THAT THEY HAE
THREE COOPERATORS AND THOSE■ORE
APPARENTLY SOME OF THE EMPLOYEES
THAT ARRANGED THE TRAVEL OF THE
UNDERAGE GIRLS TO BE WITH
EPSTEIN.
HOW SIGNIFICANT IS THAT?
>> WELL, IT'S IMPORTANT.
I MEAN, FRANKLY, I THINK THE
CASE IS GOING TO RISE AND FALL
FOR THE SOUTHERN DISTRICT OF NEW
YORK ON THE TESTIMONY OF THOSE
COOPERATORS.
THESE CASES ARE VERY DIFFICULT
TO INVESTIGATE.
THEY'RE VERY DIFFICULT TO
PROSECUTE.
OFTEN MINORS WHO ARE ABUSED HAVE
DIFFICULTY COMING FORWARD AND
TESTIFYING.
THEY HAVE DIFFICULTY, YOU KNOW,
ESSENTIALLY GOING THROUGH AND
DOING WHAT THEY WOULD NEED TO DO
TO BE A I A CASE.
SO REALLY HERE THE TESTIMONY OF
THOSE■;■;■; HAS TO BE
STRONG IN ORDER FOR THE SOUTHERN
DISTRICT TO MAKE ITS CASE IN
COURT.
AND WHAT I THINK THIS INDICTMENT
TELLS US IS THAT THE SOUTHERN
DISTRICT BELIEVES THAT THEY HAVE
TESTIMONY THAT CAN BACK THESE
CHARGES UP.
>> WHEN YOU■■■#■ DEAL
THAT WAS STRUCK, THAT RAISED SO
MANY QUESTIONS THAT THE VICTIMS
DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT, WHAT DO YOU
THINK THE QUESTIONS ARE GOING TO
BE NOW, NOT ONLY FOR ALEXANDER
ACOSTA, THE LABOR SECRETARY WHO
WAS A BIG PART OF THIS, BUT THE
JUDGE WHO SIGNED OFF ON IT?
>> YEAH, I HAVE TO SAY THERE ARE
VERY SIGNIFICANT QUESTIONS ABOUT
MR. ACOSTA'S ACTS THERE.
REALLY, THERE HAS TO BE
SOMETHING VERY SIGNIFICANT
BEHIND-THE-SCENES THAT CAUSED
THAT SERIES OF EVENTS.
THERE'S CLEARLY MISCONDUCT BY
NOT INFORMING VICTIMS.
IT APPEARS AT SOME POINT THERE
WERE MISREPRESENTATIONS THAT
WERE MADE TO THE COURT.
VERY SERIOUS MISCONDUCT BY
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT ATTORNEYS.
PARTICULARLY IN CASES LIKE THIS,
WHEN I DID INVESTIGATE SEX
TRAFFICKING CASES, THOSE VICTIMS
ARE COUNTING ON YOU AS A
PROSECUTOR.
THEY HAVE A RIGHT TO HAVE ACCESS
TO YOU AND THEY ARE COUNTING ON
YOU TO PROSECUTE AND ACT FAIRLY.
>> ANDT IS INTERESTING THAT
THE FEDERAL PROSECUTORS WORKING
ON THIS THAT ARE GOING TO HOLD
THIS PRESS CONFERENCE IN A
LITTLE UNDER AN HOUR, ARE FROM
THE SOUTHERN DISTRICT OF NEW
YORK'S PUBLIC CORRUPTION UNIT.
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU?
COULD BE THEYUST HAVE TIME E,
THEIR PLATES.
BUT IT ALSO COULD MEAN THAT
THERE'S SOME TIE TOHIS CASE,
EITHER FROM THE ANGLE YOU JUST
TALKED ABOUT OR ANOTHER, THERE'S
ON POTENTIAL OBSTRUCTION
PROVISION.
PERHAPS THERE IS A PUBLIC
OFFICIAL THAT COULD -- THAT IS
AT LEAST INVOLVED IN T CASE OUE
>> ALL REALLY IMPORTANT
QUESTIONS TO BE ANSWERED.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> ALSO THIS MORNING AS MORE
IMAGES AND REPORTS■ OFHUMANE COE
MIGRANT FIEM■■■  BORDER, THE PR
SAYS HE NOW WANTS THE MEDIA TO
GO INSIDE AND SEE FOR
THEMSELVES.
KAITLYN■■ US FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
KAITLYN, THE PRESIDENT SAYS HE
WANTS THIS, BUT THERE'S A BIG
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN SAYING THAT
AND THE FACILITIES ACTUALLY
LETTING IN JOURNALISTS WITH
CAMERASUNANNOUNCED.
>> SO FAR THEY'VE BEEN HESITANT,
NOT WANTAWMAKERS TO BRING
THEIR PHONES INTO THE
FACILITIES.
SO WHETHER OR NOT THAT
INVITATION ISNG TO GO
FORWARD IS STILL AN OPEN
QUESTION.
BUT SO FAR THE PRESIDENT AND HI
REPORTS ABOUT THESE CONDITIONS
AT THE BORDER.
HERE'S WHAT THE PRESIDENT SAID
WHEN HE WAS ON HIS WAY BACK TO
THE WHITE HOUSE YESTERDAY.
>> I'M GOING TO START SHOWING
SOME OF THESE DETENTION CENTERS
TO THE PRESS.
THEY'RE CROWDED AND WE'RE THE
ONES WHO ARE COMPLAINING ABOUT
THEY'RE CROWDED.
>> SO THE PRESIDENT THERE GOING
AFTER NOT ONLY SOME OF THOSE
DEMOCRATIC LAWMAKERS WHO HAVE
BEEN REPORTING WHAT THEY SAW
WHEN THEY'VE TOURED THESE
FACILITIES.
WE SHOULD NOTE IT'S NOT JUST ONE
SINGULAR REPORT DETAILING THESE
CONDITIONS THAT THEY SAY ARE
WIDESPREAD AT THESE FACILITIES.
OVERCROWDING AND STANDING ROOM
ONLY.
PEOPLE GOING WITHOUT HOT MEALS.
IT'S COMING FROM A REPORT FROM
THE PRESIDENT'S OWN GOVERNMENT
AND A VERY SPECIFIC IN
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" THAT■ CAME
OUT YESTERDAY AND PEOPLE SHOULD
READ.
>> AND NATASHA, YOU'RE THERE AND
YOU SPOKE TO A REP WHO SAYS
BORDER PATROL AGENTS HAVE BEEN
TRYING FOR SOME TIME TO BRING
THESE CONDITIONS TO LIGHT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, POPPY.
WE WERE TALKING TO
REPRESENTATIVE MARY GONE SQUALL
ES.
SHE REPRESENTS THE AREA WHERE
THE FACILITY IS.
SHE SAYS THAT LOCAL LEADERS LIKE
HERSELF AND THE COMMUNITY DID
NOT EVEN KNOW THAT UNACCOMPANIED
CHILDREN WERE BEING PROCESSED
THROUGH THAT FACILITY UNTIL NEWS
REPOS CAME OUT IN THE LAST
MONTH OR SO ABOUT THE CONDITIONS
INSIDE.
SHE SAID THAT SOME OF THESE
ATROL AGENTS WHOA■ LIVE IN
THIS COMMUNITY WAVE KNOWN
HER FOR A LONG TIME, THEY HAVE
BEEN TELLING HER ABOUT HOW
DEMORALIZING AND SDPRESING IT IS
TO WORK IN THE CONDITIONS
BECAUSE OF WHAT THEY ARE SEEING
DAY TO DAY WITH THE MIGRANTS.
THEY'VE ALSO TOLD HER ABOUT HOW
HUNDREDS OF CHILDREN AT ONE
POINT WERE BEING PROCESSED
THROUGH THAT FACILITY IN A SPACE
THAT'S REALLY NOT DESIGNED FOR
THAT MANY KIDS AND BEING HELD
THERE FOR LONGER THAN THEY
SHOULD BE THERE, WITH LIMITED
SHOWER AND -- SHOWER FACILITIES
TO WASH UP, LIMITED MICROWAVES
TO HEAT FOOD TO FEED THEM.
HERE'S WHAT SHE HAD TO SAY ABOUT
HER CONVERSATIONS WITH THESE
AGENTS.
>> A LOT OF THE PEOPLE I TALKED
TO WHO WORKED THERE WERE SAYING
WE HAVE BEEN TELLING HIGHER-UPS
THERE'S A PROBLEM.
AND BASICALLY THOSE PLEAS HAVE
BEEN IGNORED.
A LOT OF THE PEOPLE WHO I TALKED
TO HAVE BEEN IN THE BORDER
PATROL FOR DECADES, 23 YEARS, 24
YEARS.
THIS IS SOMETHING VERY NEW TO
THEM.
THEY WERE NEVER CHARGED WITH
BEING CARE TAKERS OF CHILDREN.
AT THE END OF THE DAY WE HAVE TO
REALIZE THAT MY COMMUNITY IS
STRUGGLING WITH AN
ADMINISTRATION-MADE PROBLEM.
>> AND GONZALEZ DID SAY THAT SHE
GOT TO VISIT INSIDE THE CLINT
FACILITY LAST WEEK WHEN THERE
WERE FAR FEWER CHILDREN.
MANY OF THEM HAVE NOW BEEN
PROCESSED OUT.
WE DID ALSO HEAR FROM THE SECTOR
CHIEF OF THE EL PASO REGION WHO
SAID NOW IN THIS REGION THEY
HAVE ONLY 26 CHILDREN IN
CUSTODY.
HE DISPUTES THEORTS OF THE
INHUMANE CONDITIONS INSIDE, BUT
HE DOES ACKNOWLEDGE IT'S VERY
POSSIBLE AGENTS HAVE BEEN
COMPLAINING ABOUT CONDITIONS AND
OVERCROWDING IN THE PAST.
HE SAYS THEY'VE ALL BEEN
COMPLAINING THAT THERE ARE JUST
TOO MANY CHILDREN AND NOT ENOUGH
RESOURCES TO PROCESS THEM
THROUGH.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR THE
REPORTING, FOR TALKING TO HER.
WE APPRECIATE IT.
>>> STILL TO COME, THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE IS TAKING
A NEW STRATEGY AS IT PUSHES TO
TRY TO GET A CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION ON THE UPCOMING CENSUS.
PLUS NEW FIGHTING WORDS WITHIN
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
HOUSE SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI TAKES
ON CONGRESSWOMAN ALEXANDRIA
OCASCIO-CORTEZ, AND LATER THE
U.S. WOMEN AREEADING HOME WITH
ANORLD CUP TITLE AND
READY TO TAKE ON A BIGGER
BATTLE, EQUAL PAY.
That Karl brought his
karaoke machine?
♪ Ain't nothing but
a heartache... ♪
No, I can't believe how easy
it was to save hundreds of
dollars on my car
insurance with GEICO.
♪ I never wanna
hear you say... ♪
No, Kevin...
no, Kevin!
Believe it!
GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
or more on car insurance.
GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
Have a discount with another
wireless carrier?
T-Mobile will match it.
Need a few more reasons to
switch?
1. Do you like Netflix? Sure you
do. That's why it's on us.
2. Unlimited data. Use as much
as you want, when you want.
3. No surprises on your bill.
Taxes and fees included.
So, if you have a discount,
bring it to T-Mobile.
We'll match it and give you
great benefits.
Be right there baby.
Whoops. Sorry.
Unlike ordinary diapers
Pampers is the first
and only diaper that
distributes wetness evenly
into three extra absorb
channels. They stay
up to three
times drier
So babies
Can sleep soundly
all night
Wishing you love, sleep
and play
Pampers
In one week...
a lot will happen in your life.
Wrinkles just
won't.
Neutrogena®
Rapid Wrinkle
Repair's
derm-proven retinol
works so fast,
it takes only one week
to reveal younger looking skin.
Making wrinkles look
so last week.
d Wrinkle Repair®
Pair with new retinol oil
for 2X the wrinkle
fighting power.
Neutrogena®
NEW TEAM, NEW ARGUMENT.
AFTER THE SUPREME COURT RULED
AGAINST THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S ATTEMPT TO ADD
A CITIZENSHIP QUESTION ON THE
CENSUS, THIS MORNING THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT SAYS A DIFFERENT TEAM
OF LAWYERS WILL NOW TAKE UP THIS
BATTLE.
FOR MORE ON WHY, JESSICA
SCHNEIDER, OUR JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT IS IN DC.
SO EVEN AFTER THE SUPREME COURT
ADMINISTRATION SEES IT AS
IMPORTANT THAT THEY'RE PUTTING A
NEW TEAM OF ATTORNEYS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, THIS WILL BE A
NEW TEAM THAT WILL NOW HAVE TO
PUSH A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT SET
OF ARGUMENTS TO TRY TO GET THE
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION ON THE 2020
CENSUS.
AND WE'VE LEARNED THAT THE
POLITICAL APPOINTEE WHO LED THE
INITIAL TEAM OF LAWYERS DID IN
FACT THINK THAT IT MADE SENSE TO
GET A NEW TEAM OF LAWYERS ON
BOARD, BECAUSE THEY'RE REALLY
DOING AN ABOUT-FACE HERE AND
IT'S A FLIP-FLOP THAT SEEMS TO
HAVE BEEN FORCED BY THE
PRESIDENT.
REMEMBER, IT WAS LESS THAN A
WEEK AGO THAT THIS FIGHT SEEMED
TO BE OVER.
LAWYERS FROM THE DOJ'S FEDERAL
PROGRAMS BRANCH TOLD THE
CHALLENGERS TO THE CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION THAT THE CENSUS WAS
GOING TO PRINT WITHOUT THE
CONTROVERSIAL QUESTION.
AND THEN THOSE LAWYERS TOLD A
JUDGE THAT THE DIVISION WAS
FINAL, BUT THEN OF COURSE WE SAW
THAT FLURRY OF TWEETS FROM THE
PRESIDENT AND HE INSISTED THAT
HE WOULD PUSH HIS ADMINISTRATION
TO FIND A WAY TO ADD THIS
QUESTION.
NOW, DOJ LAWYERS ADMITTED JUST
LAST WEEK TO A MARYLAND JUDGE IN
A HEARING ON WEDNESDAY THAT THEY
WERE REALLY BLINDSIDED BY THE
PRESIDENT'S TWEETS.
ESPECIALLY SINCE THE DOJ HAS
BEEN INSISTING ALL ALONG THAT A
JULY 1st DEADLINE TO PRINT THE
CENSUS WAS THE ABSOLUTE DROP
DEAD DEADLINE.
AND NOW ALL INDICATIONS THAT THE
DOJ IS CONTINUING TO PRESS
FORWARD TO FIND A RATIONALE TO
ADD THIS QUESTION.
THE SUPREME COURT SAID WHEN THEY
MADE THE RULING THAT IF THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT AND THE
CENSUS BUREAU WENT BACK AND
PROVIDED SOME SORT OF RATION
THIS QUESTION COULD BE ADDED.
BUT REALLY IT SEEMS
ADMINISTRATION IS RUNNING OUT OF
TIME.
THEY'VE ALREADY GONE PAST THEIR
JULY 1st DEADLINE AND NOW THEY
COULD CONTINUE TO PUSH IT
FORWARD.
WHO KNOWS IF THEY WOULD SCENE
HAVE TIME TO ADD IT.
>> AND TO YOUR POINT, NOT TO
MENTION, IF THEY COME UP WITH A
COMPLETELY NEW RATIONALE AND
REASONING, WHAT WILL THAT MEAN
FOR WILBUR ROSS' TESTIMONY WHEN
HE TALKED ABOUT THE RATIONALE,
ET CETERA.
I GUESS IF THEY WIN ON THIS, ARE
THEY GOING TO PUT AN INSERT IN
CENSUS FOR EVERYONE?
HOW WOULD THIS PLAY OUT?
>> LOGISTICALLY THAT'S SORT OF
THE BIG QUESTION HERE.
THE CENSUS WE KNOW FROM DOJ
OFFICIALS, IT HAS GONE TO PRINT
WITHOUT THAT QUESTION, BUT COULD
THE ADMINISTRATION SOMEHOW ADD
ON A CITIZENSHIP QUESTION BY
MAYBE ADDING SUPPLEMENTAL PAGES,
SUPPLEMENTAL QUESTIONNAIRES?
YOU KNOW, THE PRESIDENT HAS
FLOATED THE IDEA EVEN OF AN
EXECUTIVE ORDER TO MANDATE THAT
THIS QUESTION BE ADDED.
BUT ALL OF THESE OPTIONS, POPPY,
THEY'RE SURE TO FACE THESE
CONTINUED LEGAL FIGHTS.
WE'RE ALREADY SEEING IT ON TWO
FRONT IN FEDERAL COURTS IN NEW
YORK AND MARYLAND HERE.
AND OF COURSE WE'RE RUNNING OUT
OF TIME BECAUSE WE'RE LESS THAN
SIX MONTHS AWAY FROM 2020 AND
THE CENSUS NEEDS TO GET OUT.
>> JESSICA SCHNEIDER THANK YOU
SO MUCH.
>>> AHEAD FOR US NEW ATTACKS ON
NANCY PELOSI NANCY PELOSI'S
LEADER STYLE.
THE SPEAKER WENT OUT IN THE
LATEST NEWIP=
BATTLE?
D WINNING INTERFACE.
AWARD WINNING DESIGN.
AWARD WINNING ENGINE.
THE VOLVO XC90.
THE MOST AWARDED LUXURY
SUV OF THE CENTURY.
PNC Bank has technology to
help make banking easier,
like..
PNC Easy Lock,
so you can easily lock
your credit card
when its maximum limit differs
from its vertical limit.
and Clover Flex,
for when you need to
take credit cards
when no one carries cash.
one that hasn't followed
the family goldfish.
PNC — Make today the day.
Sun care is self care.
I used to not love wearing an
SPF
just because I felt like it was
so oily and greasy.
But with Olay Regenerist Whip
SPF 25,
it's so lightweight. I love it.
I'm Busy Philipps, and I'm
fearless to face anything.
I switched to MiraLAX
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives
forcefully stimulate
the nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX works with
the water in your
body to unblock your
system naturally.
And it doesn't cause
bloating,
cramping, gas,
or sudden urgency.
MiraLAX.
Look for the pink cap.
You're turning onto the
street
■2
when you barely
clip a passing car.
Minor accident
—no big deal, right?
Wrong. Your insurance
company is gonna raise
your rate after the other
car got a scratch so small
you coulda fixed
it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that
pen and use it to sign up
with a different
insurance company.
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because of
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN'T G
HIGH SPEED INTERNET WHERE YOU
LIVEOU CAN, WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITE INTERNET WHEREVER YO.
YOU'LL GET 25MBPS, PLUS BUILT-IN
WI-FI, AND THERE'S NO HARD DATA
LIMITS. SO, WHEREVER YOU LIVE,
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
EVERYTHING YOU LOVE ONLINE.
CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, STAY
INFORMED, WATCH THE LATEST
VIDEOS, AND HELP YOUR KIDS GET■
AHEAD. NO WONDER HUGHESNET■■■R
SATELLITE INTERNET. ACT NOW TO
SAVE BIG WITH OUR LIMITED TIME
OFFER. GET FREE STANDARD
INSTALLATION BY CALLING RIGHT
NOW. SO, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING
FOR? GET HUGHESNET GEN5. TO
ORDER, CALL THE NUMBER ON YOUR
SCREEN. BE SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR
HOME PHONE SERVICE, TOO. CALL
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN
TODAY.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
THIS MORNING DEMOCRATIC FRESHMAN
CONGRESSWOMAN ALEXANDRIA
OCASCIO-CORTEZ IS HITTING BACK
AT SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI.
PELOSI CRITICIZED HER AND THREE
OTHER DEMOCRATS FOR VOTING
AGAINST THE MEASURE FOR BORDER
FUNDING THAT EVENTUALLY PASSED
FOR THOSE DETENTION FACILITIES.
PELOSI TOLD "THE NEW YORK TIMES"
IN AN INTERVIEW, QUOTE, ALL OF
THESE PEOPLE HAVE THEIR PUBLIC
WHATEVER AND THEIR TWITTER
WORLD, BUT THEY DIDN'T HAVE ANY
FOLLOWING.
THEY'RE FOUR PEOPLE AND THAT'S
HOW MANY VOTES THEY GOT.
SO OCASCIO-CORTEZ TAKING TO WHAT
ELSE, TWITTER TO FIRE BACK,
CALLING PELOSI'S DECISION TO,
QUOTE, BLINDLY TRUST THE WHITE
HOUSE, QUOTE, A BIG MISTAKE.
MOLLY BALL IS WITH ME, NATIONAL
POLITICAL CORRESPONDENT TORE
TIME.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
AND TIFFANY, LET ME JUST BEGIN
WITH YOU.
IDEAL LOGICALLY, ON THIS THEY
COULD NOT BE MORE DIVIDED.
I DO THINK IT'S INTERESTING THAT
NANCY PELOSI HAS ALSO SAID IN
SORT OF THE MIDST OF ALL OF THIS
CRITICIZING THE MEDIA, SAYING
YOU'RE FOCUSING TOO MUCH ON
DIVISION IN THE PARTY THAN ON
THE ISSUE AT THE SOUTHERN
BORDER.
WE'RE FOCUSING A LOT ON THE
ISSUE AT THE SOUTHERN BORDER.
HOW SIGNIFICANT IS THIS DIVIDE?
>> WELL, I TAKE PELOSI'S POINT
THAT I DO THINK THERE'S THIS
CONTINUAL DRIVE THAT DEMOCRATS .
LISTEN, THIS IS AEALTHY■
GEAPPENING
WITHIN THE PARTY, AND QUITE
FRANKLY, I'M NOT HERE TO BEAT UP
ON NANCY PELOSI.
I HAT SHE'S ACHIEVED SOME
CONGRESSIONAL FEATS IN HER
TENURE.
BUT I DO THINK IN THIS INSTANCE
THAT SHE DID LOOK A BIT O OF
STEP WITH HER PARTY.
IF YOU REMEMBER,HEIME
WHEN SHE WAS GOING THROUGH
CAMPAIGNING AND TRYING TO BE
HOUSE SPEAKER AGAIN AND
CONGRESSWOMAN PRESSLEY, ONE OF
THEHO DIDN'■
THE BORDER FUNDING, SAID I'M
GOING TO VOTE FOR YOU BUT I DID
NOT ASK FOR YOUR PERMISSION TO
LEAD.
THIS IS WHAT SHE'S REC ENG
NOW.
THESE■÷ FOUR WOMEN ARE■÷
ON, THEY ARE
LAWMAKERS THAT ARE GOING TOOTE
THEIR CONSCIENCE AND■■■■EFLECT E
VIEWS OF THEIR CONSTITUENCY.
THIS IS A MAJOR DEFEAT, BECAUSE
SHE'S USED TO BEING ABLE TO WHIP
HER CAUCUS BUT AS THIS
GENERATIONAL STEP HAPPENS,
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE DISCORD AND
I DON'T THINK THAT'S A BAD THING
FOR THE PARTY.
>> IT'S INTERESTING, THE LINE
THAT REALLY STRUCK US IN THE
TIMES PIECE FROM PELOSI, IF THE
LEFT DOESN'T THINK I'M LEFT
ENOUGH, SO BE IT.
WILL THAT WORK FOR HER?
WILL SHE HAVE TO ANSWER MORE AND
MORE CALLS FROM THE LEFT?
>> WELL, WE'LL SEE.
I THINK THAT SHE'S GOING TO BE
INCREASINGLY TESTED BY THESE
DIVISIONS WITHIN THE CAUCUS.
WE'RE GOING TO SEE THIS WEEK AS
THE DEBATE HEATS UP OVER
PENTAGON FUNDING WHETHER SHE CAN
KEEP THOSE LIBERAL MEMBERS IN
THE TENT.
HER TACTIC HAS ALWAYS BEEN TO
SORT OF USE THE LEFT TO TRY ANG
YU LATE.
BECAUSE SHE IDENTIFIES AS A
LIBERAL AND SHE'S FROM ONE OF
THE MOST LIBERAL DISTRICTS IN
THE COUNT, EVEN THOUGH SHE IS
NOT NEARLY AS LIBERAL AS HER
DISTRICT IN SAN FRANCISCO.
SHE HAS ALWAYS SORT OF --
ESPECIALLY SINCE REPUBLICANS
HAVE SPENT HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS
OF DOLLARS PORTRAYING HER OF SAN
FRANCISCO LIBERALISM, SHE TAKES
THAT AND SAYS THEY CALL ME A
LIBERAL, I GUESS I AM.
THAT MEANS THAT I'M ON YOUR
SIDE.
BUT THIS IS THE MOST WE CAN GET
DONE PRACTICALLY.
I DON'T THINK THIS IS OOEL AN
IDEALOGICAL DIVISION SO MUCH AS
A TACTICAL ONE.
AND WHAT SPEAKER PELOSI IS
SAYING IS I UNDERSTAND THAT YOU
HAVE THESE IDEAS, BUT ARE YOU
WORKING WITHIN THE SYSTEM, ARE
YOU WORKING WITHIN THE PROCESS?
SO SHE'S SAYING YOU MAY HAVE
SUPPORT OUT THERE ON TWITTER OR
IN THE REAL WORD, DO YOU HAVE
SUPPORT IN THE CONFERENCE?
AND THAT'S WHAT WE'RE GOING TO
SEE, IS ARE THESE LIBERALS
WILLING TO PLAY HARD BALL WITH
THE LEADERSHIP?
ARE THEY GOING TO MAKE NANCY
PELOSI'S MORE DIFFICULT?
ALTHOUGH THERE WAS COMPLAINING,
NANCY DID GET HER VERSION
THROUGH THE HOUSE AND SHE GOT
THE SENATE BILL THROUGH THE
HOUSE.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> REAL QUICKLY, POPPY.
I HEAR YOU MOLLY AND I
COMPLETELY AGREE.
I DO THINK THIS IS AN
IDEALOGICAL AND A TACTICAL
DIVISION WITHIN THESE WOMEN.
THEY'RE ALL FOUR WOMEN OF COLOR
WHO VOTED AGAINST THIS BILL.
AND THE REALITY, I THINK THERE'S
TROUBLE RECONCILING WITHIN THIS
COUNTRY, IF THESE WERE WHITE
BABIES BEING TREATED THIS WAY IN
THESE DETENTION FACILITIES, IF
THESE WERE WHITE WOMEN BEING
HELD IN OVERCROWDED FACILITIES,
BEING TOLD TO DRINK FROM
TOILETS, THERE CERTAINLY WOULD
BE MORE OF A NATIONAL OUTCRY.
AND I THINK THAT'S SO IMPORTANT
AND RESONATING, THEY'RE SAYING
WE CANNOT TRUST THIS
ADMINISTRATION.
AND THERE'S BEEN CONTINUAL
EVIDENCE OF DONALD TRUMP
MISUSING FUNDS.
WE JUST SAW ON JULY 4th, AS A
CANDIDATE AND PRESIDENT HE HAS
MISUSED FUNDS.
SO I THINK THERE IS SOMETHING
ABOUT THESE WOMEN SAYING WHY
WOULD WE BLINDLY TRUST THIS MAN?
WE JUST FOUND OUT TODAY THAT ICE
IS USING FACIAL RECOGNITION
TECHNOLOGY.
STATES HAVEN'T PASSED LAWS TO
ALLOW THAT.
UNDOCUMENT IMMIGRANTS DIDN'T
KNOW THEY WERE TURNING THEIR
INFORMATION OVER TO ICE.
>> YOU'RE REFERENCING THE
"WASHINGTON POST" REPORTING
SAYING THAT ICE HAS BEEN USING
FACIAL RECOGNITION TECHNOLOGY TO
SCAN PHOTOS OF THE DMV OF
DRIVER'S LICENSES EVEN OF PEOPLE
NOT ACCUSED OF COMMITTING CRIMES
AND THAT RAISES A WHOLE HOST OF
OTHER QUESTIONS.
MOLLY, I FOUND THIS ATTACK
ACTUALLY ON NANCY PELOSI FROM
WOMEN'S U.S. SO■) A SECRmSTRAIG■
BI, A FIGHT FOR EQUAL
How do you gauge the
greatness of an SUV?
or to carry on a legacy? ito
Its show of strength
or its sign of intelligence?
In crossing harsh terrain
or breaking new ground?
This is the time to get
an exceptional offer
on the Mercedes of
your midsummer dreams
at the Mercedes-Benz Summer
Event, going on now.
Lease the GLA 250 SUV
for just $329 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz
Summer Event.
Mercedes-Benz.
The best or nothing.
My experience with USAA
has been excellent.
They really appreciate
the military family
and it really shows.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
another insurance company,
Wee Webber family.
We're the Tenney's
We're the Hayles,
and we're USAA members for life.
♪
Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
Did you know Congress
is working
to end
surprise medical billing?
That's when patients are hit
with medical bills
they thought would be
covered by insurance.
The problem is
big insurance companies want
a one-size-fits-all approach
that lets them decide
what they'll pay doctors
for your care.
Letting insurance companies
decide means it could be harder
for you to see the best doctors
when you need them the most.
Tell Congress,
"End surprise billing,
and don't let
insurance companies
put profits over patients.
Paid for by
Physicians for Fair Coverage.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
THIS JUST IN TO CNN, NEW YORK
GOVERNOR ANDREW CUOMO HAS JUST
SIGNED A LAW THAT WILL ALLOW
CONGRESS TO GET AHOLD OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S STATE TAX
RETURNS.
OF COURSE THIS COMES AMID THE
ESCALATING FIGHT WITH TOP
ADMINISTRATION OFFICIALS AND
CONGRESS TRYING TO GET THE
PRESIDENT'S FEDERAL TAX RETURNS.
WE'LL SEE HOW THIS DEVELOPS.
>>> WELL, FANS CHANTED EQUAL PAY
AS THE WOMEN'S NATIONAL TEAM
RECEIVED THEIR WORLD CUP MEDDLES
AFTER THEIR SECOND STRAIGHT WIN
ON SAUN.
THE TEAM IS SUING THE U.S.
SOCCER FEDERATION OVER THEIR PAY
AND THEIR STAR ISG OUT
SO MUCH■ CELEBRATETHERE, ING.■
ANDY.
SUCH A■ WIN.
BUT I WOULD ARGUE THE BIGGER
FIGHT FOR THEM IS AT HOME.
>> THAT COULD BE TRUE, POPPY.
BUT IF THERE'S EVER A TEAM THAT
THEN W THELK, IT ISRTHE U.S. WO
NATIONAL TEAM.
IT WNCREDIBL
PERFORMANCE.
THEY HAD SO MUCH ON OFF
ME. FIELD T FIGHT FOR EQUAL
BUT THIS TEAM IS STILL ABLE TO
PUT IT ALL ASIDE AND PROVE THAT
THEY ARE THE BEST TEAM IN THE
WORLD.
TEAM USA BEATING THE NETHERLANDS
2-0 IN THE FINAL.
THEY'RE ON THEIR BAY BACK TO THE
U.S.
HERE'S A PRETTY COOL PICK THEY
TOOK TOGETHER BEFORE BOARDING
THEIR PLANE.
THEY'RE GOING TO ARRIVE ABOUT
4:15 EAS GOING
TO HAVADE TOMORROW IN NEW
YORK.
RAPINOE WAS ASKED HOW THEIR
DOMINANT PERFORMANCE WILL AFFECT
THE FEDERATION'S DEFENSE AGAINST
THEM IN THEIR LAWSUIT.
>> IT'S NOT GOOD FOR THEM, IS
IT?
I MEAN, I THINK, OBVIOUSLY, IT'S
HUGE.
I THINK WE'VE BEEN A LITTLE SHY
TO SAY THAT, PUTTING SO MUCH
PRESSURE ON OURSELVES, BECAUSE I
THINK WE HAVE A CASE NO MATTER
WHAT.
OBVIOUSLY WE BROUGHT THE
LAWSUIT.
BUT THIS JUST SORT OF BLOWS IT
OUT OF THE WATER.
IT'S NOT ABOUT THAT ANYMORE,
IT'S JUST KIND OF ABOUT DOING
THE RIGHT THING.
I THINK THE FEDERATION IS IN A
UNIQUE POSITION TO KIND OF RIDE
THIS WAVE OF GOOD FORTUNE AND
GET ON BOARD AND HOPEFULLY SET
THINGS RIGHT FOR THE FUTURE.
>> THE PLAYERS IN THE U.S.
SOCCER FEDERATION WILL HEAD TO
MEDIATION SOMETIME SOON OVER
PAY.
OVER THE PAST FEW YEARS THE
WOMEN'S TEAM HAS MADE MORE
REVENUE THAN THE MEN.
THAT BEING SAID, THE MEN DID
MAKE THE WORLD CUP LAST YEAR AND
THE DIFFERENCE IS STAGGERING.
THE MEN'S CUP MADE $6 BILLION
AND PAID OUT $400 MILLION TO THE
TEAMS.
THE WOMEN'S IS EXPECTED TO
GENERATE ONLY ABOUT $130 MILLION
IN REVENUE, PAYING OUT $30
MILLION TO THE TEAMS.
THERE'S NO QUESTION THE WOMEN'S
TEAM IS MORE SUCCESSFUL.
THEY ALL KNOW THEIR NAMES AND
THEY SELL FOR JERSEYS, BUT NOW
THERE'S SO MUCH MORE MONEY IN
MEN'S SOCCER, WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO WAIT AND SEE IF THE
FEDERATION DECIDES TO GIVE THEM
A PAY RAISE.
BUT IN THE PAST THE FEDERATION
HAS ARGUED THAT THE WOMEN'S AND
MEN'S TEAMS ARE SEPARATE
ORGANIZATIONS THAT PERFORM
SEPARATE, AND THEY HAVE SEPARATE
BUDGETS THAT TAKE INTO ACCOUNT
DIFFERENT REVENUE THAT THE TEAMS
GENERATE.
>> YOU ALSO HAVE■BE ABLE TSEE T
PLACES.
THERE HAVE BEEN NETWORKS THAT
HAVE PULLED THEIR GAMES.
BEFORE YOU GO, LET'S TALK ABOUT
THE 15-YEAR-OLD TENNIS PHENOM,
COCO GAUFF BACK IN ACTION
PLAYING AT WIMBLEDON THIS
MORNING.
JUST BIG PICTURE, FOR SO MANY OF
US THAT AREN'T BIG TENNIS FANS,
THEY CAME OUT OF THE BLUE.
>> SHEñY DID AND SHE IS
A SUPERSTAR IN THE MAKING.
RIGHT NOW NOT LOOKING GOOD FOR
HER WOIBD FUTURE.
SHE LOST THE FIRST SET TO HALEP.
SHE MADE A BIG COMEBACK ON
FRIDAY.
COCO HAS REALLY BECOME A CROWD
FAVORITE AT WIMBLEDON AFTER
BEING THE YOUNGEST TO MAKE IT TO
THE FINAL ROUND IN 28 YEARS.
SHE DOESN'T TURN 16 UNTIL MARCH.
JUST AN INCREDIBLE RUN.
I MEAN, POPPY, WHEN YOU WERE 15,
COULD YOU IMAGINE DOING
SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
I KNOW I SURE COULDN'T.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WAS DOIN.
NOTHING CLOSE■k THAT.
IS REMARKABLE.
ROOTING FOR HER.
ANDY, THANK YOU.
SOON, PRESIDENT TRUMP WILL GIVE
A SPEECH, AS IN JUST A FEW HOURS
FROM NOW, TOUTING HIS RECORD ON
THE ENVIRONMENT.
REALLY?
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT.
I can't believe it.
That Karl brought his
karaoke machine?
♪ Ain't nothing but
a heartache... ♪
No, I can't believe how easy
it was to save hundreds of
dollars on my car
insurance with GEICO.
♪ I never wanna
hear you say... ♪
No, Kevin...
no, Kevin!
Believe it!
GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
or more on car insurance.
GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
Let them move the way they
were born to
in New Pampers Cruisers 360 FIT
with its ultra stretchy
waistband..
and adaptive 360  FIT
New Pampers Cruisers 360 Fit
Here's another reason to join
T-Mobile.
Unlimited data with
taxes and fees included.
No surprises on your bill.
And here's another reason to
join.
Bring in your discount, and
we'll match it.
That's right, T-Mobile will
match your discount.
♪♪
Corey is living with metastatic
breast
which is breast cancer
that hd
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking IBRANCE
with an aromatase inhibitor,
which is for
postmenopausal women
or for men with HR+/ HER2-
metastatic breast cancer■
as the first hormonal
based therapy.
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease progression
versus letrozole.
Patients taking IBRANCE
can develop
low white blood cell counts,
which may cause serious
infections
that can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE, tell your
doctor if you have
fever, chills, or other signs of
pregnant, breast feeding,dne
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side-effects include
low red blood cell and
low platelet counts,
infections, tiredness, nausea,
sore mouth,
abnormalities in liver blood
tests, diarrhea,
hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash, and
loss of appetite.
Corey calls it her new normal,
because a lot has changed.
But a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about IBRANCE,
the number-one prescribed,
FDA-approved
oral combination treatment
for HR+/HER2- MBC.
In one week...
a lot will happen in your life.
Wrinkles just
won't.
Neutrogena®
Rapid WrinRepa's
derm-proven retinol
works so fast,
it takes only one week
to reveal younger looking skin.■
Neutrogena®
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
■ ■■@('1■8■8■2s2■1Cz■zCz■zGs■a■■
What do all these people
have in common, LiMu?
[ guttural grunt ]
Exactly. Nothing!
They're completely
different people.
That's why they
make customized
car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need.
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done it again, LiMu.
[ LiMu grunts ]
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
>>> ALL RIGHT.
SO IN JUST A FEW HOURS PRESIDENT
TRUMP WILL GIVE A SPEECH AS THE
WHITE HOUSE PUTS IT, QUOTE, TO
RECOGNIZE HIS ADMINISTRATION'S
ENVIRONMENTAL LEADERSHIP AND
AMERICA'S LEADING ROLE IN THE
WORLD.
BUT HIS SPEECH WOULD FOLLOW
MAJOR STEPS IN MISS
ADMINISTRATION TO REVERSE OVER
80 ENVIRONMENTAL REGULATIONS PUT
IN PLACE UNDER THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE FACTS HERE.
OUR CHIEF CLIMATE CORRESPONDENT
IS WITH ME AND FORMER EPA DPIN
STRART UNDER THE GEORGE W. BUSH
ADMINISTRATION AND FORMER
GOVERNOR OF NEW JERSEY.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU BOTH.
SO WE'RE GOING TO HEAR FROM THE
ADMINISTRATION ON THIS TODAY AND
WE'LL GET TO SORT OF WHY THEY'RE
DOING THIS IN A MOMENT.
LET ME JUST OUTLINE FOR EVERYONE
WHAT THIS ADMINISTRATION'S OWN
EPA SAID IN A REPORT THAT CAME
OUT IN APRIL.
HERE ARE THE THINGS THAT ARE
HAPPENING BECAUSE OF THE CLIMATE
CRISIS, HURRICANE STORM
INTENSITY, FREQUENCY AND
DURATION WILL INCREASE, MORE
INTENSE DROUGHTS, WARMER
TEMPERATURES CAUSING MORE WILD
FIRES AND THIS IS THE
PRESIDENT'S OWN EPA WARNED TO
ANTICIPATE A COMBINATION OF
IMPACTS, FLOODS AND FIRES WHICH
MAY BE INTENSIFIED BECAUSE OF
THE CHANGING CLIMATE.
FROM WHAT YOU'VE SEEN THE
EVIDENCE, NOT THE RHETORIC, IS
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION TAKING
THIS SERIOUSLY ENOUGH AT ALL?
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
AND THEY'RE ROLLING BACK
REGULATIONS IN A WHOLE LOT OF
OTHER AREAS THAT ARE MAKING
PEOPLE'S LIVES LESS HEALTHY.
THEY'RE A THREAT SO US IN SO
MANY DIFFERENT WAYS.
THE CLIMATE CRISI■■ IS■■ ONE OF.
PRETENDING IT DOESN'T EXIST
DOESN'T STOP IT, DOESN'T MAKE IT
GO AWAY.
>> NO MATTER WHAT YOU SAY.
SOME OF WHAT'S BEEN ROLLED BACK,
BILL, INCLUDES OBVIOUSLY PULLING
OUT OF THE PARIS CLIMATE
AGREEMENT, LOWERING THE CAR
EMISSION STANDARDS THAT HAD BEEN
INCREASED TO STOP SO MUCH
POLLUTION, WEAKENING THE CLEAN
POWER PLAN FROM THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION, ELIMINATING THE
EPA PANEL ON POLLUTION AND
OPENING UP ANWAR WHICH YOU'VE
DONE A LOT OF REPORTING ON.
>> YES.
THE PRESIDENT IS OLD ENOUGH TO
REMEMBER WHEN YOU COULD TASTE
THE AIR IN LOS ANGELES AND WHEN
THE CUYAHOGA RIVER IN OHIO WAS
ON FIRE.
AND TODAY YOU CAN SWIM THE
CUYAHOGA.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
AND YOU CAN GO TO LA AND SEE THE
MOUNTAINS.
THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN BY ACCIDENT.
IT HAPPENED WHEN NIXON SIGNED
THE CLEAR AIR AND WATER ACT, AND
THEN 40 YEARS OF DELIBERATE LAW
MAKING TO GRIND THIS THING OUT
WHY YOU CAN SAY THE AIR IS
CLEAR.
NEW ZEALAND BLOWS US AWAY.
BUT WHAT'S LOST IN THIS CLEAN
AIR, CLEAN WATER TODAY MESSAGING
IS THAT HE SHOULD BE SAYING --
STEP TO THE MICROPHONE AND SAY
WHEN BARON IS MY AGE, LIFE AS WE
KNOW IT WILL BE COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT.
>> BECAUSE IT ISBOUT OUR
CHILDREN.
>> IT IS.
>> IT'S ABOUT THE FUTURE.
AND HE HAS A YOUNG CHILD, AS YOU
BRING UP.
SO LISTEN TO OBVIOUSLY THE
PRESIDENT HAS TOUTED THIS AND
TALKED ABOUT AMERICA'S AIR AND
WATER AS BEING AT A RECORD
CLEAN, HIS WORDS.
AND THEN THE VICE PRESIDENT,
MIKE PENCE ON WITH JAKE TAPPER
JUST A FEW WEEKS AGO MADE THIS
ARGUE.
LISTEN.
>> AMERICA HAS THE CLEANEST AIR
AND WATER IN THE WORLD.
WE'LL CONTINUE TO USE --
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
WE DON'T HAVE THE CLEANEST AIRE.
WE DON'T.
YOU GET BACK TO ME WITH SOME
STATISTICS.
>> WE'RE MAKING PROGRESS ON
REDUCING CARBON EMISSIONS.
>> I MEAN, JAKE LAUGHED BECAUSE
IT IS LAUGHABLE, BECAUSE IT'S
JUST NOT TRUE.
SO WHAT ARE YOUR CONCERNS AHEAD
OF THE SPEECH WHEN THE
ADMINISTRATION IS PUTTING OUT
JUST BLATANT UNTRUTHS ABOUT THE
ENVIRONMENT?
>> MY KWERN IS THAT PEOPLE SEEM
TO TAKE WHAT HE SAYS AND SAY HE
MAY NOT BE TELLING THE WHOLE
TRUTH BUT WE DON'T CARE.
THIS IS THE MOMENT WITH WE
REALLY NEED TO CARE ABOUT THIS.
IT IS ABOUT OUR CHILDREN AND OUR
GRANDCHILDREN.
IT'S ABOUT THE FUTURE AND MAKING
OUR LIVES HEALTHIER, MAKING OUR
ECONOMY GREATER, WHICH WE CAN DO
AND WE'VE DONE IT OVER TIME AS
YOU POINTED OUT WHEN WE STARTED
THE EPA WITH A CLEAN AIR ACT AND
CLEAN SAFE DRINKING WATER, WE
SAW THE POPULATION GROW, WE SAW
THE REAL GPP MORE THAN DOUBLE,
WE SAW OUR ENERGY USE CLIMB.
AND YET WE WERE ABLE TO GROW OUR
ECONOMY AT EXTRAORDINARY RATES.
SO IT'S NOT AN EITHER-OR THING
AND WE HAVE GOT TO GET OVER THIS
IDEA THAT IT IS AND SOMEHOW
DOING AWAY WITH REGULATIONS IS
GOING TO MAKE EVERYTHING HAPPY.
>> BILL, YOU'VE DONE SO MUCH
REPORTING ON THIS.
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE THE CASE
THAT PROTECTING THE ENVIRONMENT
HURTS BUSINESS.
IT MEANS YOU TRANSFORM BUSINESS?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AS THE GOVERNOR POINTS OUT, WE
DIDN'T GO INTO A 40-YEAR
RECESSION WHEN WE STARTED
WORRYING ABOUT BREATHABLE AIR.
BUT THE OTHER THING THAT, YOU
KNOW, THE BIG PICTURE STORY THAT
WE'RE JUST NOT WIRED AS HUMAN
BEINGS TO WORRY ABOUT.
WE DON'T THINK INE EARTH LONG
TIME FRAMES.
WE THINK IF THAT NOISE BEHIND
THAT ROCK IS GOING TO EAT ME.
BUT IF YOU TAKE A STEP BACK AND
REALIZE THAT EVERY 2.7 SECONDS A
PIECE OF THE ARCTIC ICE TURNS TO
WATER AND IT'S BEENT WAY FOR
40 YEARS.
SO AGAIN, BARON TRUMP WILL NOT
GET A 30-YEAR MORTGAGE IN MIAMI,
BECAUSE IT WILL CHANGE THE
TOPOGRAPHY OF OUR LAND.
>> THE ADMINISTRATION WE HEAR,
BILL, A LOT TALK ABOUT NATURAL
GAS AND THE PUSH FOR NATURAL GAS
AND REPLACING COAL, PARTS OF
COAL WITH THAT AND HOW THAT, YOU
KNOW, ESSENTIALLY SOLVES THINGS.
IT HAPPENS, RIGHT?
BUT IT DOESN'T AT ALL ADDRESS
THE BIG ISSUE, DOES IT?
>> EVERYTHING IS CLEANER THAN
COAL.
WE COULD BURN WHALES AGAIN AND
IT WOULD BE AN IMPROVEMENT OVER
COAL, BUT IT'S STILL
EXACERBATING THE PROBLEM.
SOLAR AND WIND HAS INCREASED AND
GOTTEN CHEAPER, IT HASN'T
REPLACED FOS ILL FUELS.
WE'RE BURNING EVERYTHING.
NUCLEAR MIGHT BE -- SHOULD BE
PART OF THE CONVERSATION.
>> I THINK A TRANSITION, THAT
NAUK CLEAR IS WHAT WE'VE GOT TO
LOOK AT BECAUSE WE'VE GOT THESE
NUCLEAR REACTORS THAT PRODUCE NO
REGULATED POLLUTANTS OR
GREENHOUSE GASES WHILE THEY'RE
PRODUCING POWER.
AND WE SEEM TO BE CLOSING THEM
DOWN, WHICH I THINK IS A
PROBLEM.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO BUILD ANY
MORE BIG ONES, BUT SMALL
MODULAR, WE COULD CREATE JOBS
THAT WOULD BE GOOD FOR THE
ECONOMY.
THAT'S THE NEW WAVE UNTIL THE
RENEWABLES GET TO BE BASED
POWER, NOT JUST SHAVINGS THAT
ARE ON 24/7.
THEN WE CAN GO WITH THAT.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE'LL BE WATCHING AGAIN.
THE PRESIDENT IS GOING TO GIVE
THIS ADDRESS IN JUST A FEW
■
YOU SHOULD WATCH IT OR READ THE
ENTIRE THING.
>>> RIGHT THIS.  JUST■í
AMERICAN TENNIS PHENOM COCO
GAUFF'S MAGICAL RUN AT WIMBLEDON
HAS ENDED.
SHE JUST LOST IN STRAIGHT SETS
TO FORMER NUMBER ONE RANKED
PLAYER SIMONA HALEP.
THE R-OLD WAS THEOUNGEST
PLAYER TO MAKE IT TO THE ROUND
OF 16 IN 28 YEARS.
CONGRATS TO HER FOR MAY BEING IT
SO FAR.
I THINK WE'RE GOING TO BE
WATCHING HER FOR MANY, MANY
YEARS TO COME.
>> MINUTES FROM NOW THE FBI AND
U.S. ATTORNEY WILL BE GIVING A
PRESS CONFERENCE.
THEY'RE ANNOUNCING REALLY
SERIOUS SEX TRAFFICKING CHARGES
AGAIN BILLIONAIRE JEFFREY
EPSTEIN.
HE'S ACCUSED OF RUNNING A RING
AND SEXUALLY ABUSING DOZENS OF
UNDERAGE GIRLS.
YOU'LL SEE THE PRESS CONFERENCE
LIVE HERE IN JUST A FEW MINUTES.
THIS IS CRITICALLY IMPORTANT.
STAY WITH CNN.
At Subaru, wing on
distracted d
with sensors that alert you when
your eyes are off the road.
The all-new Subaru Forester.
The safest Forer.
When I book at Hilton.com
I get to select my room
from the floor plan...
Free Wi-Fi...
...and the Price
Match Guarantee.
Hiltere is no catch.
Yeah the only catch
is I'm never leaving.
No I'm serious,
I live here now.
Book at Hilton.com
t the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
Hmm. Exactly.
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay for
what you need.
Nice. But, uh...
what's up with
your... partner?
Oh. Well, we just spend
all day telling everyone
how we customize
car insurance,
because no two people
are alike, so...
LiMu gets a
little confused
when he sees
another bird
that looks
exactly like him.
[ loud crash ]
Yeah.
He'll figure it out.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
♪♪
Play it cool and escape
heartburn fast
with new TUMS Chewy
Bites Cooling Sensation.
♪ TUM TUM TUM TUMS ♪