>>> REFUGEES COMING TO AMERICA
HAVE TRIED TO BUILD A BETTER
LIFE.
MANY STRUGGLE TO FIND JOBS WITH
UPWARD MOBILITY.
THIS WEEK'S CNN HERO HELPS
REFUGEES SHOWCASE THEIR TALENTS.
MEET CARRIE BRODY.
>> WHAT WE'RE TEACHING OUR
STUDENTS ISN'T JUST KNIFE SKILLS
OR COOKING.
IT'S THE IDEAL THAT YOU HAS A
HUMAN HAVE VALUE.
WHAT'S THE DREAM TEAM COOKING
UP?
AWESOME.
>> THAT EXPERIENCE OF WATCHING
STUDENTS TRANSFORM, SEEING
REALLY COME INTO THEIR OWN,
IN1
INSPIRES ME.
>> TO LEARN MORE, GO TO
CNNHEROES.COM.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
OUR COVERAGE CONTINUES.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
JOHN BERMAN HERE FOR ANDERSON.
AND WE BEGIN WITH THIS BREAKING
NEWS.
DID THE PRESIDENT JUST THREATEN
TO BLOCK THE RELEASE OF THE
MUELLER REPORT?
WE DON'T KNOW FOR SURE BUT
DEPENDING ON HOW YOU READ WHAT
HE JUST WROTE, HE MIGHT HAVE.
A LITTLE BACKGROUND FIRST.
THIS AFTERNOON IN A LETTER TO
CONGRESS ATTORNEY GENERAL BILL
BARR SAID THE MUELLER REPORT
WILL BE READY FOR RELEASE BY
MID-APRIL IF NOT SOONER.
THAT FULL REPORT IS NEARLY 400
PAGES EXCLUDING TABLES AND
APPENDICES.
THAT WAS MID-AFTERNOON.
JUST MINUTES AGO THE PRESIDENT,
THE SAME PRESIDENT WHO OVER THE
PAST WEEK HAS SAID HE'S FOR THE
FULL RELEASE OF THE REPORT WROTE
THIS.
ROBERT MUELLER WAS A HERO TO THE
RADICAL LEFT DEMOCRATS UNTIL HE
RULED THAT THERE WAS NO
COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA, SO
RIDICULOUS TO EVEN SAY, AFTER
MORE THAN TWO YEARS SINCE THE
INSURANCE POLICY STATEMENT WAS
MADE BY A DIRTY COP, I GOT THE
ANSWERS I WANTED, THE TRUTH.
THE PROBLEM IS NO MATTER WHAT
THE RADICAL LEFT DEMOCRATS GET,
NO MATTER WHAT WE GIVE THEM, IT
WILL NEVER BE ENOUGH.
JUST WATCH.
THEY WILL HARASS AND COMPLAIN
AND RESIST, THE THEME OF THEIR
MOVEMENT, SO MAYBE WE SHOULD
JUST TAKE OUR VICTORY AND SAY
NO.
WE'VE GOT A COUNTRY TO RUN.
SO MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST TAKE OUR
VICTORY AND SAY NO?
WHAT EXACTLY DOES THAT MEAN?
IS HE NOW THREATENING TO BLOCK
THE RELEASE OF THE REPORT OR IS
HE JUST BROADLY SAYING NO TO
WHAT HE CALLS THE HARASSMENT AND
COMPLAINING?
HONESTLY, WE DON'T KNOW.
WE'RE ASKING, BUT WE DON'T HAVE
AN ANSWER AS OF YET.
WE ALSO DON'T KNOW WHAT'S IN THE
NEARLY 400 PAGES OF THE REPORT.
DEMOCRATS HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'S IN
THEM.
THE WHITE HOUSE AND FELLOW
REPUBLICANS DON'T KNOW WHAT'S IN
THEM.
IN FACT, BARR TOLD CONGRESS IN
THAT LETTER THAT HE HAS NO PLANS
TO SHARE THE REPORT WITH THE
WHITE HOUSE BEFORE IT'S MADE
PUBLIC, OR SHOULD WE SAY BEFORE
MORE OF IT IS MADE PUBLIC.
IN FACT, AS OF NOW BARR REVEALED
74 WORDS FROM MUELLER'S REPORT
IN THAT FOUR-PAGE SUMMARY.
74 WORDS EXCLUDING A SINGLE
FOOTNOTE AND THE TITLE OF THE
REPORT.
IF YOU INCLUDE ALL OF THAT IT
JUMPS TO A WHOPPING 101 WORDS.
YES, THOSE WORDS DO INCLUDE THE
FACT THAT MUELLER DOES NOT THINK
THERE IS A CRIMINAL CASE FOR
COORDINATION OR CONSPIRACY, BUT
101 WORDS OUT OF 400 PAGES
LEAVES A LOT OF ROOM FOR
POSSIBILITIES.
DO THE 400 PAGES EXONERATE THE
PRESIDENT AS HE'S BEEN CLAIMING
FOR THE PAST FIVE DAYS SINCE WE
RECEIVED THE BARR SUMMARY?
OR DO THE 400 PAGES REVEAL
DETAILS ABOUT KEY EVENTS ABSENT
FROM IT?
DETAILS LIKE WHAT MR. MUELLER'S
TEAM FOUND OUT ABOUT THE TRUMP
TOWER MEETING.
DETAILS LIKE WHAT THEY LEARNED
ABOUT THE COVER-UP AND LIES
ABOUT THE TRUMP TOWER MEETING.
DETAILS LIKE WHAT THEY LEARNED
ABOUT THE TRUMP SCOW
PROJECT THAT THE PRESIDENT
PURSUED UNTIL THE END OF HIS
CANDIDACY BUT DENIED EVER DOING.
DETAILS LIKE WHAT THEY LEARNED
ABOUT THE OVAL OFFICE MEETING
WITH RUSSIAN AMBASSADOR SERGEY
KISLYAK.
DETAILS LIKE WHY THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL SPECIFICALLY DID NOT
EXONERATE THE PRESIDENT ON
THE QUESTION OF OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE.
THE REPORT WILL COME OUT,
ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR SAYS, ONCE
THE DOJ IS FINISHED SCRUBBING
THE REPORT OF SENSITIVE
INTELLIGENCE AND ONGOING LEGAL
MATTERS.
AND THEY'RE GETTING HELP WITH
THOSE RETRACTIONS FROM THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL HIMSELF.
MEANWHILE, DEMOCRATS ARE
DEMANDING THAT BARR STICK TO THE
DEADLINE THEY SET FOR THE
RELEASE OF THE REPORT WITHOUT
REDACTIONS.
THAT DEADLINE IS TUESDAY, APRIL
2nd.
NOW, THE NEWS ON ALL OF THIS
BROKE LATE THIS AFTERNOON JUST
BEFORE PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS SET
TO TALK TO THE PRESS, SO THERE
IS REACTION FROM HIM ON CAMERA
AND THEN THERE'S THAT TWEET HE
JUST SENT OUT.
CNN'S KAITLIN COLLINS JOINS US
NOW FROM THE WHITE HOUSE WITH
THE DETAILS.
IS THERE ANY SENSE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE WHAT THE PRESIDENT MEANS
WITH THIS STATEMENT OF SAYING NO
MAYBE TO THE RELEASE OF THE FULL
REPORT?
>> Reporter: SO FAR, JOHN, WE
HAVEN'T GOTTEN A LOT OF CLARITY.
IF YOU READ THROUGH THE
PRESIDENT'S TWEET, THE BEGINNING
OF IT IS ESSENTIALLY WHAT HE'S
BEEN SAYING THE LAST SEVERAL
DAYS, BUT IT'S THAT LAST
SENTENCE RIGHT THERE AT THE
END THAT REALLY CATCHES YOUR EYE
WHERE HE SAYS MAYBE WE SHOULD
JUST TAKE OUR VICTORY AND SAY
NO.
THAT IS WHAT IS GOING TO HAVE
PEOPLE TALKING OVER THE NEXT FEW
DAYS, WONDERING WHAT IT IS THE
PRESIDENT IS TRYING TO SAY THERE
BECAUSE IT'S CERTAINLY NOT
EXPLICIT.
JOHN, ONE THING IT COULD BE IS
THAT LETTER FROM THE HOUSE
JUDICIARY CHAIRMAN, JERRY
NADLER, IN RESPONSE TO BILL BARR
EARLIER TODAY WHERE HE
ESSENTIALLY REFUTED EVERYTHING
BARR SAID IN HIS LETTER.
HE SAID HE DIDN'T AGREE WITH
WHEN BARR SAID THAT LETTER WAS
GOING TO MAKE IT TO CONGRESS.
HE DIDN'T AGREE TO THE FACT
THERE WERE GOING TO BE
REDACTIONS IN IT.
AND HE DIDN'T LIKE IT WHEN BARR
SAID HE WOULD COME TESTIFY IN
MAY AND NADLER SAID HE WANTED
HIM TO COME TESTIFY NOW.
SO THAT COULD BE PART OF WHAT
THE PRESIDENT IS REFERRING TO.
BUT ALSO IN THE LAST SEVERAL
DAYS, I'VE TALKED TO SEVERAL OF
THE PRESIDENT'S ALLIES WHO HAVE
BEEN TOUTING BARR'S SUMMARY ON
SUNDAY SAYING THAT IT'S A
VICTORY FOR THE PRESIDENT.
BUT THEY'RE ALSO A LITTLE BIT
WORRIED ABOUT THE FULL REPORT
COMING OUT, ALL 400 PAGES.
NOT THAT IT'S GOING TO EXPOSE
THE PRESIDENT LEGALLY OR
CRIMINALLY TO ANYTHING, BUT THEY
FEAR IT COULD BE POLITICALLY
DAMAGING TO PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> YOU KNOW, IT IS INTERESTING
BECAUSE EARLIER TODAY IN PUBLIC
THE PRESIDENT DID SEEM TO DEFER
TO THE ATTORNEY GENERAL IN TERMS
OF THE REPORT'S RELEASE,
CORRECT?
>> Reporter: TOTALLY.
HE WAS SPEAKING WITH REPORTERS
IN PALM BEACH.
THEY ASKED HIM ABOUT THE
BREAKING NEWS FROM BILL BARR
ABOUT SENDING THIS REDACTED
REPORT TO CONGRESS WITHIN A
MATTER OF WEEKS.
THE PRESIDENT SEEMED PRETTY
ONBOARD WITH WHAT BARR HAD SAID.
>> I HAVE GREAT CONFIDENCE IN
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL.
IF THAT'S WHAT HE'D LIKE TO DO,
I HAVE NOTHING TO HIDE.
THIS WAS A HOAX.
THIS WAS A WITCH HUNT.
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NOTHING TO
HIDE.
I THINK A LOT OF THINGS ARE
COMING OUT WITH RESPECT TO THE
OTHER SIDE.
BUT I HAVE A LOT OF CONFIDENCE
IN THE ATTORNEY GENERAL.
>> Reporter: NOW, WE SHOULD NOTE
THAT IN BARR'S LETTER TODAY HE
SAID THE WHITE HOUSE IS NOT
GOING TO GET THEIR HANDS ON A
COPY OF THIS REDACTED REPORT
UNTIL IT'S IN LAWMAKERS' HANDS
AS WELL.
HE SAID IN THAT LETTER THE WHITE
HOUSE HAS THE RIGHT TO ASSERT
ANY EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE BUT
SINCE THE PRESIDENT HAS PUBLICLY
DEFERRED TO HIM AS HE DID THERE
ON CAMERA, THAT BARR IS GOING TO
BE THE ONE MAKING THOSE
DECISIONS.
SO, JOHN, THE QUESTION IS, IS
BARR GOING TO TRY TO ASSERT SOME
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE FOR ANY
CONVERSATIONS THAT THE PRESIDENT
HAS HAD THAT IS IN THAT REPORT?
>> WE'LL PUT THAT QUESTION TO
SOME OF OUR BEST LEGAL MINDS IN
JUST A MOMENT.
KAITLIN COLLINS, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
JOINING US FROM "THE NEW YORK
TIMES," MAGGIE HABERMAN, ALSO A
CNN POLITICAL ANALYST.
AND SOMETHING OF A TRUMP HUMAN
DECODER RING.
MAGGIE, THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH
US.
THIS LATEST STATEMENT FROM THE
PRESIDENT, MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST
SAY NO.
I HAVE A HARD TIVING
THAT THIS IS A REAL, LITERAL,
GENUINE THREAT TO BLOCK THE
RELEASE OF THE MUELLER REPORT.
IS THIS JUST MORE OF, "A," HIM
MESSING WITH PEOPLE ON A FRIDAY
NIGHT BECAUSE HE CAN?
OR, "B," SORT OF MOVING THE BAR,
NO PUN INTENDED, SO THE PART OF
THE REPORT THAT DOES GET
RELEASED BY BARR, HE CAN SAY,
LOOK, WE'RE BEING COMPLETELY
TRANSPARENT.
I DIDN'T HAVE TO BE.
>> IT COULD BE ALL OF THE ABOVE.
I THINK SOME OF THESE TWEETS OF
HIS WHERE THERE'S NOT MUCH
UTILITY IN TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT THE MOTIVE IS.
IN THIS ONE HE COULD BE TROLLING
THE PRESS VERY SUCCESSFULLY
RIGHT NOW, HE COULD BE REACTING
TO TELEVISION COVERAGE WHICH HE
OFTEN DOES, OR HE COULD INDEED
BE THINKING, AND I TEND TO THINK
IT'S A LITTLE LESS THAT, THAT
HE'S SETTING THE BAR AT A
DIFFERENT POINT.
LOOK, I UNDERSTAND WHY THE WHITE
HOUSE FEELS VERY GOOD OVER THE
PAST WEEK AND THEY'RE DOING
EXACTLY WHAT I THINK THAT THEIR
POLITICAL OPPONENTS WOULD
PROBABLY DO IN THE SAME
SITUATION, WHICH IS SAY, LOOK,
THIS EXONERATES -- HE'S CLEARED.
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
BEING CLEARED CRIMINALLY AND A
POLITICAL PROBLEM.
THIS REPORT IS A POTENTIAL
HE SAID VERY CLEARLY IN THAT
VIDEO, I HAVE NOTHING TO HIDE.
SO IF HE'S SAYING THAT, BARR IS
GOING THROUGH IT FOR GRAND JURY
TESTIMONY, SOURCES AND METHODS,
THINGS LIKE THAT.
BARR CAN FLAG AREAS OF POTENTIAL
PRIVILEGE BUT MY UNDERSTANDING
IS HE CAN'T EXERT PRIVILEGE.
HE CAN ONLY DO THAT IF HE TALKS
TO THE PRESIDENT.
AND THAT'S UP TO THE PRESIDENT.
>> WE'LL TALK TO OUR LAWYERS
COMING UP ABOUT THAT.
IT IS POSSIBLE THAT THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL COULD WITHHOLD THINGS
BETHE PRESIDENT MIGHT
ASSERT EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE AT
SOME POINT, LIKE WE SEE IN
CONGRESSIONAL HEARINGS.
I DO WANT TO ASK YOU BECAUSE
KAITLIN SAID SOME OF HER
REPORTING IS A SENkLITTLE
TREPIDATION ABOUT THE UNKNOWN,
ABOUT WHAT MIGHT BE IN THESE 400
PAGES.
WHAT ARE YOU HEARING ON THAT
FRONT?
>> EXACTLY THAT.
AS TIME HAS GONE ON, THERE IS A
RECOGNITION THAT I THINK THE
INITIAL HIGH OF THE SUMMARY FROM
LAST SUNDAY HAS WORN OFF A BIT.
YOU SAW TODAY THAT BARR SENT
EITHER SOME NOTE OR MADE A
STATEMENT THAT THIS WAS REALLY
JUST TOP LINE FINDINGS, FOLKS.
THIS WAS NOT SUPPOSED TO BE
INDICATIVE OF THE ENTIRE REPORT.
I THINK AS TIME IS GOING ON,
FOLKS AROUND THE PRESIDENT ARE
BECOMING MORE AWARE OF THE FACT
THAT THERE COULD BE THINGS THAT
ARE POLITICALLY DAMAGING IN
HERE.
IT MAY TURN OUT THAT THERE ISN'T
MUCH, BUT AT 300 TO 400 PAGES
THAT AS I UNDERSTAND IT DON'T
INCLUDE THE INDICTMENTS OR
PIECES OF EVIDENCE, THERE IS
GOING TO BE A FAIR AMOUNT OF
INFORMATION THERE.ACTLY WHAT TH
REFLECTS ON THE PRESIDENT
REMAINS TO BE SEEN, BUT THEY
DON'T KNOW EITHER.
SO, THEY'RE GETTING A LITTLE
AHEAD OF THEMSELVES ON SOME OF
WHAT THEY'RE SAYING AND TRYING
TO GET THE HEADLINES THEY WANT.
POLITICALLY, I UNDERSTAND THAT.
THEY'RE TRYING TO MUDDY THE
WATERS ON THIS BEFORE IT ALL
COMES OUT.
>> WHAT IS THE OPINION RIGHT NOW
THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS OF HIS
ATTORNEY GENERAL?
YOU GET THE SENSE THAT HE'S HIS
FAVORITE PERSON ON EARTH AT THE
CURRENT MOMENT.
>> THE PRESIDENT'S ESTIMATION OF
PEOPLE CAN CHANGE PRETTY
QUICKLY, AS YOU KNOW.
I THINK THAT HE WAS VERY HAPPY
WITH THE LETTER THAT CAME OUT ON
SUNDAY.
HE WAS VERY HAPPY THAT THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL INSERTED
HIMSELF INTO THIS IN TERMS OF
SAYING THERE'S NO OBSTRUCTION
IN THE A.G. RULES.
I THINK DEPENDING ON WHAT
HAPPENS WITH THIS REPORT, WE
WILL SEE HOW HAPPY HE IS.
>> THE ATTORNEY GENERAL AND THE
PRESIDENT BOTH CLAIM THERE'S A
SEPARATION, THAT THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL IS DOING THIS COMPLETELY
ON HIS OWN.
>> AND THEY NEED THAT TO BE THE
VIEW, BECAUSE OTHERWISE THERE IS
GOING TO BE A PERCEPTION -- IT
MAY NOT BE REAL BUT THERE WILL
BE A PERCEPTION BY SOME THAT THE
WHITE HOUSE GOT INVOLVED AND
PERHAPS MUCKED AROUND WITH IT.
BARR IS ALREADY GETTING A LOT OF
CRITICISM FOR HAVING TAKEN THE
MUELLER REPORT FURTHER THAN
MUELLER SEEMS TO HAVE.
>> ANY EVIDENCE IT'S NOT
COMPLETELY ON HIS OWN, AND "B,"
DOES THE WHITE HOUSE TRUST HIM
TO DO IT ON HIS OWN?
>> I THINK THE WHITE HOUSE DOES
TRUST HIM TO DO IT ON HIS OWN.
I THINK THEY THINK VERY HIGHLY
OF BILL BARR.
I THINK THE WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL'S OFFICE HAS A GOOD
RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM.
THERE'S NO REASON TO BELIEVE
FROM ANYTHING I KNOW RIGHT NOW
THAT THERE IS SOME KIND OF
EXCHANGES GOING ON ABOUT THE
INFORMATION.
BUT WE HAVE ANOTHER IT SOUNDS
LIKE TWO WEEKS UNTIL WE SEE
THIS, SO WHO KNOWS WHAT'S
HAPPENING.
>> MAGGIE, STAND BY IF YOU WILL.
I WANT TO BRING IN JOHN DEAN,
ALSO CNN LEGAL ANALYST SHAN WU
WHO BRIEFLY DEFENDED RICK GATES
WHEN HE WAS INDICTED BY THE
MUELLER TEAM.
JOHN, LET ME START WITH YOU ON
THE QUESTION MAGGIE AND I WERE
DISCUSSING THERE.
WE WERE TOLD THE WHITE HOUSE
WILL NOT SEE THIS BEFORE BARR
RELEASES IT.
IT WOULD BE THE WHITE HOUSE WHO
WOULD HAVE TO TECHNICALLY ASSERT
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE.
BUT WHAT'S YOUR UNDERSTANDING OF
WHAT WILLIAM BARR COULD DO HERE?
COULD HE IDENTIFY AREAS AND KEEP
THEM REDACTED BECAUSE OF THE
POSSIBILITY THAT EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE MIGHT COVER THEM?
>> HE COULD THEORETICALLY DO
THAT.
I KNOW OF NO INSTANCE WHERE A
PRESIDENT HAS DELEGATED OR TRIED
TO DELEGATE EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE
RIGHTS AND POWERS.
SO I THINK WHAT WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT IS, ARE THERE THINGS THAT
ARE GOING TO COME UP IN THE
REPORT THAT WERE GIVEN UNDER THE
CONDITION BY THE WHITE HOUSE
WHERE THEY PROVIDED DOCUMENTS TO
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL AND THEY
SAID THEY WERE RESERVING THE
RIGHT TO INVOKE EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE.
WILL BARR FLAG THAT AND WITHHOLD
IT FOR SOME REASON UNTIL THE
PRESIDENT DOES OR DOES NOT
INVOKE EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE?
>> SO, SHAN --
>> THAT'S THE ISSUE.
>> WE KNOW THAT WILLIAM BARR IS
AN ACCOMPLISHED LAWYER.
I THINK THERE'S BEEN EVIDENCE
OVER THIS LAST WEEK THAT HE'S A
SHREWD POLITICAL PLAYER AS WELL.
I DON'T MEAN THAT PEJORATIVELY.
BUT THE MERE FACT THAT THIS
REPORT IS 400 PAGES, NEARLY, AND
WE LEARNED THAT TODAY OFFICIALLY
FROM HIM FOR THE FIRST TIME.
THERE'S NO REASON HE COULD NOT
HAVE TOLD US THAT LAST FRIDAY
HAD HE WANTED TO, CORRECT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IT WAS LIKE PULLING TEETH TO GET
THAT PAGE COUNT OUT.
HE'S NOT IN THE REALM RIGHT NOW
WHERE HE'S CONFINED BY LEGAL
REQUIREMENTS, SO IT VERY MUCH IS
HIM EXERCISING HIS DISCRETION.
ONE OF THE POINTS JOHN JUST
RAISED IS QUITE FASCINATING.
ONE OF THE GREAT UNKNOWNS IS, WE
DON'T KNOW WHAT KIND OF
CONDITIONS THERE WERE WITH
REGARD TO INFORMATION TURNED
OVER BY THE WHITE HOUSE TO HIM.
IN FACT, WE DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT WHAT HE PROMISED WITH
REGARD TO THE PRESIDENT'S
WRITTEN ANSWERS AS WELL.
ALL THAT HAS GIVEN BARR AN
ENORMOUS AMOUNT OF DISCRETION.
AND HE APPEARS VERY UNAFRAID TO
USE THAT DISCRETION, JOHN.
>> HE LISTED FOUR AREAS, SHAN,
WHERE HE WOULD REDACT OR
WITHHOLD MATERIAL IN THESE 400
PAGES.
GRAND JURY TESTIMONY,
INTELLIGENCE TESTIMONY, ALSO
ONGOING LEGAL INVESTIGATIONS AND
NUMBER FOUR, I WANT MORE
EXPLANATION ON.
INFORMATION THAT WOULD UNDULY
INFRINGE ON THE PERSONAL PRIVACY
AND REPUTATIONAL INTERESTS OF
PERIPHERAL THIRD PARTIES.
THAT MIGHT BE AN AREA WHERE
THERE IS WIDE DISCRETION.
I WOULD IMAGINE SOME ARGUMENT,
SHAN.
>> OH, YES, THAT IS A AREA OF
VERY WIDE DISCRETION.
THAT'S LIKE HIS SAFETY NET THERE
FOR WHAT HE WANTS TO DO.
IT SOUNDS LIKE THE MUELLER
REPORT IS WHAT WE CALL A
PROSECUTION MEMO.
AND THAT'S GOING TO RELY HEAVILY
ON THE GRAND JURY INFORMATION.
USUALLY THERE'S TONS AND TONS OF
QUOTES FROM THAT IN THE
ANALYSIS.
IT'S NOT ROCKET SCIENCE TO GET
RID OF THE GRAND JURY TESTIMONY.
IT'S QUITE EASY.
ANYTHING THAT CAME BEFORE THE
GRAND JURY.
IF HE TAKES THAT OUT OF THE
EQUATION, NOT TOO MUCH LEFT.
HE TAKES OUT CLASSIFIED, NOT TOO
MUCH LEFT.
SOURCES, TECHNIQUES, NOW YOU'VE
GOT REALLY SMALL AMOUNTS.
IF HE THEN EXERCISES THIS LAST
ONE, WHICH HE THINKS IS
SENSITIVE MATERIAL IN HIS
JUDGMENT, YOU COULD BE LOOKING
AT JUST PAGES AND PAGES OF BLANK
PAGES.
>> THERE'S A LITTLE BRISTLING IN
HERE, TOO, MAGGIE, IN THIS NEW
LETTER FROM WILLIAM BARR WHERE
HE SAYS IT'S BEEN
MISCHARACTERIZED THAT HIS
FOUR PAGES WERE A SUMMARY.
HE'S NOW SAYING IT WASN'T A
SUMMARY, IT WAS PRINCIPAL
CONCLUSIONS.
HE OBVIOUSLY DOESN'T LIKE HOW
THIS IS BEING PORTRAYED.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT THE FIVE
DAYS OF COVERAGE THAT HAVE BEEN
SUGGESTING THAT HE BASICALLY
PRESENTED A FINDING BEFORE
ANYBODY HAS SEEN THE REPORT,
ANYBODY OUTSIDE OF THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT HAS SEEN THE REPORT,
I THINK THAT SEEMS TO HAVE
BOTHERED HIM.
AGAIN, I THINK THIS ALL -- I
DON'T KNOW, TO BE CLEAR, I
REALLY WANT TO BE CAREFUL ABOUT
WHAT WE DO NOTW, WHICH IS A
LOT.
WEAT'S IN THIS
REPORT.
BUT SEEING SOMETHING LIKE THIS
AFTER HIS INITIAL LETTER TO
CONGRESS LAST SUNDAY, IT
INDICATES TO ME THAT HE WANTS TO
AT LEAST PREPARE THE PUBLIC OR
CONGRESS FOR THE FACT THAT THERE
MIGHT BE, YOU KNOW, SORT OF MORE
NUANCED PORTRAYALS, SHALL WE
SAY, IN THE REPORT THAN JUST
SAYING THERE'S NO EVIDENCE OF
CONSPIRACY AND A LACK OF
EXONERATION OR A CHARGE ON
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE, BUT I'VE
DECIDED NO OBSTRUCTION.
>> HE WANTS TO PREPARE US FOR
THAT NOW.
WHERE ONE WEEK AGO HAD HE TOLD
THE PUBLIC THERE WERE 400 PAGES
THERE MIGHT HAVE BEEN A
DIFFERENT RESPONSE.
>> THAT IS ONE AREA WHERE I
THINK THERE IS A LEGITIMATE
CRITICISM, WHY THEY COULDN'T SAY
THAT OUT FRONT.
I DO THINK BARR WAS IN A DAMNED
IF HE DID, DAMNED IF HE DIDN'T
POSITION OVER THE WEEKEND.
HE GOT CRITICIZED OF JUST TAKING
48 HOURS.
IF HE DIDN'T, HE WOULD BE
ACCUSED OF MEDDLING AROUND.
I DON'T THINK HE HAD A WIN-WIN
THERE.
BUT I DO THINK THAT IN TERMS OF
JUST PREPARING PEOPLE FOR AS
MUCH INFORMATION ABOUT THE SCOPE
OF THIS, I THINK THAT WOULD HAVE
BEEN WISE.
>> JOHN DEAN, KEY HISTORICAL AND
LEGAL QUESTION HERE.
ONE AREA WHERE BARR SAYS HE WILL
WITHHOLD INFORMATION FROM THIS
REPORT HAS TO DO WITH GRAND JURY
TESTIMONY.
WELL, A JUDGE CAN RELEASE THAT
GRAND JURY TESTIMONY AND MAKE IT
PUBLIC.
THERE'S HISTORICAL PRECEDENT FOR
THAT, IN KEN STARR'S
INVESTIGATION, ALSO THE
WATERGATE INVESTIGATION.
MY UNDERSTANDING IN WATERGATE,
ONE OF THE AREAS WHERE THIS
BECAME A REASON TO MAKE IT
PUBLIC WAS BECAUSE THERE WAS AN
OFFICIEACHMENT INQUIRY.
DOES THAT INCENTIVIZE
CONGRESS -- NOW, THEY DON'T WANT
TO DO THIS.
DEMOCRATS DON'T WANT TO USE
IMPEACHMENT REALLY IN ANY WAY
RIGHT NOW.
BUT MIGHT THEY NEED TO, TO MAKE
THE LEGAL CASE THAT THEY HAVE A
RIGHT TO SEE THE GRAND JURY
TESTIMONY?
>> JOHN, THERE'S NOT A LOT OF
CASE LAW ON THIS.
THERE ARE A HANDFUL OF CASES.
THERE'S SOME CONFLICTING CASES.
THE D.C. CIRCUIT HAS BEEN VERY
FAVORABLE TO CONGRESS.
BUT AS YOU POINT OUT, IT'S BEEN
IN THE IMPEACHMENT CONTEXT.
NOT JUST PRESIDENTS, BUT JUDGES.
AND SO THEY WANT TO SEE -- IT'S
A VERY DIFFERENT SITUATION WHEN
IT'S JUST A GENERAL OVERSIGHT
INQUIRY.
THE CASE LAW IS VERY MIXED
THERE.
SO, THIS IS NO SURE ROUTE.■
IF THEY DO ISSUE A SUBPOENA THAT
THEY CAN GET THIS MATERIAL VIA
SUBPOENA, THE GRAND JURY
MATERIAL
THEY CAN PROBABLY GET EVERYTHING
SURROUNDING THE GRAND JURY AND
LEARN LARGELY WHAT DID HAPPEN IN
A GRAND JURY.
THEY CAN GET NOTES FROM
PROSECUTORS.
THEY CAN GET OTHER THINGS THAT
WEREN'T ACTUALLY PRESENTED IN A
GRAND JURY, FBI SUMMARIES, BUT
THE GRAND JURY ITSELF, THE 6-E
RULE IS VERY TIGHT.
>> SHAN, ONE OTHER FASCINATING
THING IN THESE TWO PAGES THAT WE
GOT FROM WILLIAM BARR, HE MADE A
POINT OF SAYING THAT THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL, NOT THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S TEAM, THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL IS ASSISTING HIM IN
GOING THROUGH THIS 400-PAGE
REPORT.
TO ME, THAT FEELS LIKE A
MESSAGE, THAT MUELLER IS BUYING
IN.
MAY NOT BE TRUE, I DON'T KNOW.
BUT IT'S A MESSAGE THAT BARR
WANTS TO DELIVER THAT MUELLER IS
BUYING INTO WHAT BARR IS DOING.
>> IT DOES SOUND LIKE A MESSAGE.
FROM A PRACTICAL STANDPOINT,
JOHN, YOU'D HAVE TO HAVE THE
MUELLER TEAM'S ASSISTANCE IN
SCRUBBING WHAT'S THE GRAND JURY
MATERIAL AND ONGOING
INVESTIGATIONS.
SO, THAT'S REALLY SORT OF A
PRACTICAL POINT THAT HE PUTS OUT
THERE, BUT IT CERTAINLY HAS THE
IMPLICIT ATMOSPHERIC THAT THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL IS BUYING INTO
EVERYTHING THAT WE DO.
>> MUELLER WAS NOT A PART OF THE
FOUR-PAGE SUMMARY LAST WEEK, SO
THAT HE'S A PART OF THIS NOW IS
INTERESTING.
SHAN, JOHN, MAGGIE, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
>>> A LOT MORE AHEAD FOR US
TONIGHT, INCLUDING A DISCUSSION
WITH THE MAN WHO'S BEEING t
FOR THE IMPEACHMENT OF THEr#■#E.
ISING TO BACK DOWN AFTER
THE BARR SUMMARY AND AS
DEMOCRATS HAVE QUIETED TALKS OF?
>>> AND LATER, PRESIDENT TRUMP
IS WARNING THAT HE WILL CLOSE
THE BORDER WITH MEXICO AS EARLY
AS NEXT WEEK.
WHAT IS BEHIND THIS NEW THREAT
AND THE NEW DEADLINE?
WE'LL HAVE THE LATEST AHEAD.@■■■
The right gear...
matters.
Introducing the all-new
2019 Ford Ranger,
It's the right gear.
With a Terrain Management
System for... this.
al for...ate for... that.x>r
Yeah... this.
Heading to the supermarket?
Get any truck.
Head Heading out here?rket?
Get the Ford Ranger.
The only adventure gear
Built Ford Tough.
They're our parents...
■
neighbors... loved ones.
Living with diseases like
cancer, epilepsy,
mental health conditions
and HIV.
Maybe you're one of them.
But new Medicare rules could
deny access to the latest,
most effective therapies...
therapies that keep
them healthy.
Are Me%that save less
than one percent
worth the risk to millions of
patients?[
■@■@ent Trump promised■hú ■ ■ ■.
[farmers bell]
(Driver)
Relax, it's just a bug.
That's not a bug,
that's not a bug!
(Burke)
Hit and Drone.
we've seen a thing or two.7 kne
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
úúú
So, recently my son's band was
signed by a record label.
While we're on the road,
I can keep my parents
in the loop with
the whole FaceTime thing.
I created a rockstar.
(both laughing)
(announcer)
The best network is even better
when you share it.
Buy the latest iPhone
and get iPhone 10R on us.
Each day Justin
chooses to walk.
He does it all with
Dr. Scholl's..7÷7■sxC7
Only Dr. Scholl's has
Massaging Gel Insoles
that provide
all-day comfort.
To keep him feeling
more energized.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to Move.
%=%=%
Behr presents: Tough as Walls.
♪
That's some great paint.
BEHR ULTRA, a top-rated
interior and exterior paint.
Paint, prime, protect -
all in one.
Now that's some great paint!
Find it exclusively
at The Home Depot.
>>> AGAIN, OUR BREAKING NEWS,
ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR SAYS HE
WILL DELIVER THE MUELLER REPORT,
OR MOST OF IT, TO CONGRESS BY
MID-APRIL IF NOT SOONER.
A REPORT THAT BARR SAYS IS
NEARLY 400 PAGES LONG.
WHATEVER HAPPENS NEXT, HOUSE
SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI SAYS THAT
FOR NOW, IMPEACHMENT IS NOT ON
THE TABLE.
DEMOCRATS, SHE SAYS, SHOULD
FOCUS ON HEALTH CARE AND THE
ECONOMY.
THAT IS NOT WHAT MY NEXT GUEST
THINKS.
HE'S TOM STEYER, FOUNDER OF NEED
TO IMPEACH.
TOM, THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH
US.
ROBERT MUELLER SAYS THERE WAS NO
CRIMINAL COORDINATION OR
CONSPIRACY WITH RUSSIA.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL SAYS
THERE WAS NO CRIMINAL
OBSTRUCTION.
NO DEMOCRATS WANT TO GO DOWN
THIS ROAD, TO SAY NOTHING OF THE
COMPLICATIONS IT POSES FOR THE
PRESIDENT.
WHY ARE YOU GOING TO THE MAT ON
THIS?
>> JOHN, WE'RE A GRASSROOTS
ORGANIZATION.
8 MILLION PEOPLE HAVE SIGNED OUR
PETITION ASKING THAT THE
PRESIDENT BE IMPEACHED.
WHAT WE'RE ASKING FOR IS TO PUT
THE EVIDENCE IN FRONT OF THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
WE'VE SAID FOR A YEAR, DON'T
WAIT FOR THE MUELLER REPORT.
BUT WHEN THE MUELLER REPORT
COMES, LET'S LOOK AT THE
INFORMATION.
WE ALREADY KNOW FROM THE PUBLIC
RECORD THAT THIS IS THE MOST
CORRUPT PRESIDENT IN AMERICAN
HISTORY.
AND I BELIEVE WE'VE SEEN HIM
OBSTRUCT JUSTICE.
SO I BELIEVE WHAT WE REALLY WANT
TO DO IS PUT THE EVIDENCE IN
FRONT OF THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
THROUGH PUBLIC HEARINGS, THROUGH
GIVING US HIS TAX RECORDS, AND
BY GIVING US THE FULL MUELLER
REPORT SO WE, THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE ACROSS THE COUNTRY, CAN
DECIDE FOR OURSELVES WHETHER HE
DID -- WHETHER WHAT HE DID WAS
OBSTRUCT JUSTICE AND BREAK HIS
VOW TO US AND TO THE
CONSTITUTION.
>> LET ME PUT IT THIS WAY.
WE'VE ONLY SEEN 101 WORDS THAT
ARE DIRECT QUOTES FROM THE
MUELLER REPORT.
BUT AMONG THEM ARE, HE SAYS HE
COULD NOT OR WILL NOT ESTABLISH
A CRIMINAL CASE FOR CONSPIRACY
OR COORDINATION.
IS THERE ANYTHING THAT COULD BE
IN THESE 400 PAGES, ANYTHING
THAT ROBERT MUELLER COULD SAY
THAT WOULD CONVINCE YOU TO DROP
YOUR PURSUIT OF IMPEACHMENT?
>> JOHN, I HAVEN'T SEEN THE
MUELLER REPORT.
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN THE MUELLER
REPORT.
>> I KNOW THAT.
>> YOU CAN'T --
>> BUT I'M JUST TRYING TO
ESTABLISH WHETHER --
>> I WILL SAY THIS.
>> OKAY.
WE WILL LOOK AT THE INFORMATION
THERE, WHICH HAS BEEN GATHERED
OVER TWO YEARS AND TRY AND
UNDERSTAND WHAT IT MEANS.
BUT WE HAVE IN THE PUBLIC RECORD
THAT THIS IS A PRESIDENT WHO'S
REFUSED TO DIVEST HIMSELF FROM
HIS BUSINESS, WHO'S CONTINUED TO
DO BUSINESS WITH FOREIGN
GOVERNMENTS AND WITH AMERICAN
CORPORATIONS OVER WHOM HE HAS A
LOT OF CONTROL --
>> AND THAT'S MY QUESTION.
ARE YOU FOR IMPEACHMENT NO
MATTER WHAT THE MUELLER REPORT
SAYS, ASIDE FROM ANYTHING THAT
MIGHT BE IN THERE?
>> THERE IS SOMETHING IN THERE
THAT I WILL LOOK AT VERY CLOSELY
AND I BELIEVE HONESTLY AND
OBJECTIVELY, WHICH IS WHAT IS
THE INFORMATION THAT HE'S
GATHERED ON OBSTRUCTION.
BUT IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT ME AND I
THINK THAT'S THE POINT, JOHN.
THERE'S A QUESTION HERE ABOUT
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE GETTING TO
SEE THIS.
NOT THE INSIDERS IN WASHINGTON,
D.C., NOT THE ADMINISTRATION
DECIDING WHETHER THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN CORRUPT
AND LAWLESS.
GIVE IT TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
SO WE CAN TAKE A LOOK AND LET ME
SAY, THERE IS A REAL QUESTION
HERE ABOUT WHETHER THE PRESIDENT
IS GOING TO BE TREATED EQUALLY
BEFORE THE LAW LIKE EVERY OTHER
AMERICAN.
>> WHAT ABOUT WHAT -- WHAT ABOUT
WHAT NANCY PELOSI SAYS, WHICH IS
THAT SHE WOULD RATHER THE
DEMOCRATS IN CONGRESS FOCUS ON
OTHER THINGS?
>> WELL, LET ME SAY THIS.
CONGRESS HAS FULL CAPABILITY,
AND I'VE ASKED THEM DIRECTLY,
NOT ONLY TO GO FORWARD AND TRY
TO PASS LEGISLATION ON HEALTH
CARE AND THE ECONOMY, BUT THEY
ALSO HAVE THE ABILITY AT THE
SAME TIME TO HOLD PUBLIC
HEARINGS AND LET THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE SEE WHAT HAS GONE ON
HERE.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S A CONFLICT
AT ALL.
BUT WHAT I DO THINK IS TRUE IS
WE CANNOT NORMALIZE THE KIND OF
CORRUPT BEHAVIOR THAT THIS
PRESIDENT HAS SHOWN BEFORE AND
DURING HIS ADMINISTRATION.
FOR INSTANCE, WE KNOW FROM THE
ONE DAY OF PUBLIC HEARINGS THAT
WE'VE SEEN, WHICH WAS THE
TESTIMONY OF MICHAEL COHEN
BEFORE THE HOUSE OVERSIGHT
COMMITTEE THAT THE PRESIDENT WAS
INVOLVED IN FELONIES WHILE HE
WAS IN THE WHITE HOUSE.
SO FROM MY STANDPOINT, WE NEED
TO HAVE A SERIES OF HEARINGS, SO
AMERICANS CAN LOOK AND SEE WHO
THE PRESIDENT SURROUNDS HIMSELF
WITH AND WHAT KINDS OF
ACTIVITIES THEY WERE INVOLVED
WITH TOGETHER AND LET US MAKE UP
OUR MINDS.
THIS IS A POLITICAL QUESTION,
NOT A CRIMINAL QUESTION.
THIS IS A POLITICAL QUESTION
ABOUT WHETHER THIS PRESIDENT IS
CORRUPT AND WHETHER HE'S PUT HIS
INTERESTS AHEAD OF THE INTERESTS
OF THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
>> TOM STEYER, THANK YOU FOR
JOINING US TONIGHT.
WE LOOK FORWARD TO SPEAKING TO
YOU MORE.
MAYBE IN A COUPLE OF WEEKS WHEN
ALL OF US HAVE ACTUALLY SEEN
WHAT'S IN THIS REPORT.
>> THAT WOULD BE A GOOD THING,
JOHN.
>>> WE HAVE MORE BREAKING NEWS
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS HE WILL
CLOSE THE ENTIREN BORDER
OR LARGE PARTS OF IT BY NEXT A8C
ISG ITS PART TO STOP
ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION.
COMING UP, CAN HE ACTUALLY DO
THAT?■■■■ HAPPEN IF HE
L■■&IW■
■■■■Y■Y■Y■
■■■
-Omar, look.
[ Thunder rumbles ]
Omar, check this out.
Uh, yeah, I was calling to see
if you do laser hair removal.
For men.
Notice that my hips
are off the ground.
[ Engine revving ]
And then, I'm gonna pike
my hips back into downward dog.
[ Rhythmic tapping ]
Hey, the rain stopped.
-A bad day on the road
still beats a good one off it.
-Tell me about
that dental procedure again!
-I can still
taste it in my mouth!
-Progressive
helps keep you out there.
>>> MORE BREAKING NEWS TONIGHT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS THREATENING
TO CLOSE THE BORDER BETWEEN THE
UNITED STATES AND MEXICO AS
EARLY AS NEXT WEEK, SAYING
THERE'S NO MORE DETENTION SPACE
TO HOLD UNDOCUMENTED IMMIGRANTS.
LAST NIGHT IN A BLISTERING
SPEECH TO SUPPORTERS IN
MICHIGAN, HE SAID A LARGE PART
OF THE PROBLEM WERE FRAUDULENT
ASYLUM SEEKERS WANTING TO ENTER
THE UNITED STATES.
>> YOU HAVE PEOPLE COMING UP --
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE ALL MET BY THE
LAWYERS.
THE LAWYERS HAVE -- AND THEY
COME OUT.
THEY'RE ALL MET BY THE LAWYERS.
AND THEY SAY, SAY THE FOLLOWING
PHRASE.
I AM VERY AFRAID FOR MY LIFE.
I AM AFRAID FOR MY LIFE.
OKAY.
AND THEN I LOOK AT THE GUY.
HE LOOKS LIKE HE JUST GOT OUT OF
THE RING, HE'S THE HEAVYWEIGHT
CHAMPION OF THE WORLD.
IT'S A BIG FAT CON JOB, FOLKS.
>> SO IF THE PRESIDENT ACTUALLY
GOES THROUGH WITH THE DRASTIC
MOVE OF CLOSING THE BORDER, IT
WOULD NOT ONLY STOP PEOPLE BUT
ALSO BILLIONS IN TRADE.
JOINING ME NOW, FORMER
REPUBLICAN SENATOR RICK SANTORUM
AND DEMOCRATIC STRATEGIST MARIA
CARDONA.
SENATOR, LET ME START WITH YOU,
CLOSING THE ENTIRE BORDER.
AS A PRO BUSINESS REPUBLICAN,
ARE YOU IN FAVOR OF CLOSING THE
ENTIRE BORDER WITH MEXICO?
>> I'M CERTAINLY NOT FROM A
BUSINESS PERSPECTIVE.
IT'S NOT A BENEFIT TO OUR
COUNTRY, IT'S NOT A BENEFIT
CERTAINLY TO THE PEOPLE IN THE
SOUTHWEST.
I MEAN, IT WOULD BE DEVASTATING
TO THEM.
BUT IT DOES SEND A MESSAGE AND
IT SENDS A MESSAGE TO MEXICO.
THAT'S REALLY WHERE THE MESSAGE
NEEDS TO BE SENT.
YOU'VE GOT LITERALLY NOW -- EVEN
THOSE ON THE LEFT ARE ADMITTING
THAT WE'VE GOT A CRISIS DOWN
THERE WITH THE HUGE NUMBERS OF
PEOPLE NOW COMING.
ALL COMING NOT FROM MEXICO BUT
TRAVELING THROUGH MEXICO.
SO THIS IS SOMETHING THE MEXICAN
GOVERNMENT COULD DO SOMETHING
ABOUT IF THEY WANTED TO BUT
THEY'RE NOT DOING SOMETHING
ABOUT IT AND THAT'S WHAT I THINK
THE MESSAGE -- YOU KNOW, THE
MESSAGE OF DOING SOMETHING MORE
DRAMATIC AT THE BORDER IS
DIRECTED AT THEM.
>> IS THAT HOW YOU SEE IT,
MARIA?
>> NO, ABSOLUTELY NOT, JOHN.
I THINK WHAT THIS PRESIDENT BOTH
SAID IN HIS THREATS ABOUT
CLOSING THE BORDER AND IN HIS
DISGUSTING MOCKERY OF ASYLUM
SEEKERS TELLS US THAT HE HAS NO
IDEA HOW TO FIX THE IMMIGRATION
SYSTEM, AND WORSE, HE'S NOT EVEN
INTERESTED IN FIXING IT.
HE IS USING THIS AS A CLARION
CALL FOR HIS BASE.
THAT IS IT.
YES, WE DO HAVE A PROBLEM, WE DO
HAVE A CRISIS AT THE BORDER.
GUESS HOW YOU FIX IT.
YOU ACTUALLY FOCUS ON REAL
SOLUTIONS.
YOU FIGURE OUT WHAT IT'S GOING
TO TAKE TO HELP THESE PEOPLE
STAY IN THEIR OWN COUNTRIES.
THAT'S GOING TO TAKE DIPLOMATIC
RELATIONS.
THAT'S GOING TO TAKE PEOPLE
UNDERSTANDING WHAT IS GOING ON
IN CENTRAL AMERICA AND ACTUALLY
HELPING TO FIX AND RESOLVE AND
STABILIZE THEIR ECONOMY AND
THEIR GOVERNMENT.
HERE'S THE PROBLEM, JOHN.
TO FIX THIS LONGSTANDING
IMMIGRATION PROBLEM, IT'S GOING
TO BE HARD.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE BIPARTISAN
SOLUTIONS BASED POLICY, AND IT'S
GOING TO TAKE A REAL FOCUS ON
DOING THIS IN A HUMANE WAY.
DONALD TRUMP DOESN'T DO HARD.
DONALD TRUMP DOESN'T DO
SOLUTIONS-BASED POLICY.
AND DONALD TRUMP CERTAINLY DOES
NOT DO HUMANE.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE LANGUAGE,
SENATOR, THAT MARIA WAS TALKING
ABOUT THERE.
THE MOCKING LANGUAGE CALLING IT
A CON JOB FROM THESE ASYLUM
SEEKERS, WHO AS YOU KNOW ARE
COMING FROM EL SALVADOR AND
COUNTRIES RIDDLED BY VIOLENCE.
YOU KNOW, AS A MAN OF DEEP
FAITH, AS I KNOW YOU ARE, IS
THAT THE RIGHT WAY TO TALK ABOUT
THESE PEOPLE WHO COME TO THIS
COUNTRY SAYING THEY'RE
SUFFERING?
>> WELL, WHAT HE'S DOING --
LOOK, I DON'T LIKE THE
PRESIDENT'S TONE WHEN HE DOES
THOSE TYPES OF MOCKERIES.
I THINK IT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT
THE PRESIDENT SHOULD BE DOING.
HAVING SAID THAT, HE DOES POINT
OUT THAT, LOOK, A GREAT
NUMBER -- A FAIRLY HIGH
PERCENTAGE OF ASYLUM SEEKERS DO
NOT SUCCEED IN THEIR ASYLUM AND
DON'T HAVE LEGITIMATE CLAIMS.
I THINK YOU CERTAINLY CAN MAKE
THAT CASE BY THE NUMBERS.
HE MAKES IT BY MOCKERY AND
DRAMA, AND THAT WAY WE TALK
ABOUT IT.
IF YOU MADE IT BY THE NUMBERS,
NO ONE WOULD TALK ABOUT IT.
THAT'S JUST THE WAY THE
PRESIDENT COMMUNICATES.
YOU CAN LIKE IT OR NOT LIKE IT,
BUT HE DOES GET HIS POINT
ACROSS.
WE HAVE PEOPLE TALKING ABOUT IT.
LOOK, TO ANSWER MARIA'S ISSUE
THAT THE PRESIDENT DOESN'T DO
HARD, THE IDEA THAT SOMEHOW OR
THE OTHER THAT WE'RE GOING TO
STEM THE TIDE OF PEOPLE COMING
TO THIS COUNTRY BY DIPLOMATIC OR
EMERGENCY OR ECONOMIC AID TO EL
SALVADOR AND GUATEMALA, YOU WANT
TO TALK ABOUT LONG TERM, THAT'S
LONG TERM.
THE SHORT-TERM PROBLEM WHICH IS
REAL HAS TO BE DEALT WITH AND
THAT IS RELATIVELY EASY IF THE
MEXICANS DECIDE THEY WANT TO
PARTICIPATE IN STEMMING THAT
TIDE.
>> RICK, BEFORE I LET MARIA
ANSWER THAT, SENATOR, ARE YOU
SAYING YOU WOULDN'T USE THE TYPE
OF LANGUAGE THE PRESIDENT USES
HERE.
BUT MAKING FUN OF ASYLUM
SEEKERS, MAKING FUN OF PEOPLE
FLEEING VIOLENCE, ARE YOU REALLY
SAYING THAT'S AN EFFECTIVE WAY
OF MAKING AN ARGUMENT?
>> I'M SAYING THE PRESIDENT'S
EXAMPLE, I DON'T KNOW IF YOU
WANT TO CALL IT MAKING FUN.
>> HE CALLED IT A CON JOB AND
SAID --
>> HE WAS MAKING FUN.
>> WHAT I WOULD SAY IS THAT
THERE ARE PROBABLY CIRCUMSTANCES
THAT FIT THE BILL.
I DON'T THINK IT'S AN
APPROPRIATE WAY TO DO IT, BUT AS
I SAID, IT'S EFFECTIVE IN THE
SENSE THAT IT GETS PEOPLE TO
TALK ABOUT THE POINT OF THE
NUMBER OF PEOPLE WHO COME OVER
HERE WHO SIMPLY DO NOT QUALIFY
FOR ASYLUM AND NEVER WOULD AND
SHOULDN'T BE.
>> GO AHEAD, MARIA.
>> BUT, SENATOR, HOW IS THAT
HELPING TO FIX THE PROBLEM BY
MOCKING THESE PEOPLE?
WHY DOESN'T HE SIT DOWN WITH
PEOPLE WHO ARE ACTUALLY EXPERTS
AT HOW YOU FIX ASYLUM?
AND THE ISSUE IS ACTUALLY NOT
PEOPLE WHO ARE TRYING TO GAME
THE SYSTEM.
THE ISSUE ISN'T EVEN ACTUALLY
MONEY, BECAUSE IMMIGRATION --
HOMELAND SECURITY GOT A TON MORE
MONEY IN THE CR THAT WE JUST
PASSED, THE ISSUE THAT WE ARE
MISSING IS ACTUALLY PEOPLE THAT
ARE WANTING TO AND WILLING TO
SIT DOWN AND FOCUS ON A
SOLUTION.
I CAN TALK ABOUT TWO QUICK
SOLUTIONS RIGHT NOW, SENATOR,
THAT WOULD HELP TO STEM THE
TIDE.
SPEND SOME MONEY ON ADDITIONAL
IMMIGRATION JUDGES TO SET UP
ASYLUM INTERVIEWS ON THE BORDER
AND THEN YOU TRY TO DO THESE
CASES AND DO THEM QUICKLY.
THAT'S ONE VERY QUICK THING.
BUT AGAIN, THIS PRESIDENT IS NOT
INTERESTED IN SOLUTIONS.
HE'S INTERESTED IN USING THESE
PEOPLE TO HELP HIS OWN POLITICAL
SITUATION.
>> WE ARE INTERESTED IN
SOLUTIONS HERE AND WE WILL TALK
ABOUT THEM AGAIN VERY SOON.
SENATOR SANTORUM, MARIA CARDONA,
THANKS FOR BEING WITH US.
I APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> UP NEXT, LEGENDARY NEWS
REPORTER AND ANCHOR SAM
DONALDSON JOINS US TO TALK ABOUT
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S NEW ATTACKS ON
THE MEDIA AND HOW THE REPUBLICAN
NATIONAL COMMITTEE IS REPORTEDLY
GATHERING EVIDENCE TO USE
AGAINST REPORTERS WHO COVER THE
WHITE HOUSE.@■@■ @■ v v■v v v
h.
Ok.
Nasty nightime heartburn?
Try Alka-Seltzer PM Gummies.
The only fast, powerful
heartburn relief,
plus melatonin so you can
fall asleep quickly.
Oh, what a relief it is!
At Fidelity,■8■p■p■plear p■4 p
■;
as well as all the things
you want to do.
Because when you're ready
for what comes next,
the only direction is forward.
♪♪
Ñ■■@ñ■ú■"ç■■■F■
♪ 'Cos I know what it means ♪
♪ To walk along the lonely
street of dreams ♪
♪ Here I go again on my--- ♪
You realize your vows are a
Whitesnake song?
Ñ=do.Ñ=
If you ride, you get it.
GEICO Motorcycle.
15 minutes
could save you 15% or more.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS BACK IN
ATTACK MODE AND HE'S TAKING AIM
AT ONE OF HIS FAVORITE TARGETS.
LAST NIGHT BEFORE A FRIENDLY
CROWD IN GRAND RAPIDS, MICHIGAN,
THE PRESIDENT SPENT A GOOD CHUNK
OF HIS 85-MINUTE SPEECH GOING
AFTER DEMOCRATS AND THE MEDIA,
WHO HE CLAIMS KNEW ALL ALONG
THAT HE NEVER COLLUDED WITH
RUSSIA.
>> THE CORRUPT MEDIA, AND IT'S
NEVER BEEN MORE CORRUPT THAN IT
IS TODAY.
THE MEDIA BOSSES, BAD PEOPLE.
THE CROOKED JOURNALISTS, THE
TOTALLY DISHONEST TV PUNDITS.
BY THE WAY, THEY KNOW IT'S NOT
TRUE.
THEY JUST GOT GREAT RATINGS.
>> SO, SLAMMING THE MEDIA IN
FRONT OF CROWDS OF SUPPORTERS IS
NOT NEW FOR THIS PRESIDENT.
WHAT IS NEW, THE RNC AND
PRO-TRUMP SUPER PAC, AMERICA
FIRST, ARE REPORTEDLY PLANNING
ON TAKING IT A STEP FURTHER.
A SOURCE TELLS "THE ATLANTIC"
THE ORGANIZATIONS ARE PREPARED
TO HIT REPORTERS WITH 30-SECOND
SPOTS HIGHLIGHTING THEIR, QUOTE,
RIDICULOUS CLAIMS ABOUT
COLLUSION.
THE SOURCE ALSO CLAIMS THE
REPORTERS' TWEETS HAVE BEEN
SCREENCAPPED AND IT'S ALL READY
TO GO.
AWARD-WINNING JOURNALIST SAM
DONALDSON JOINS US NOW.
SAM, YOU KNOW ATTACKS ON
COVERAGE IS NOT NEW BUT A PAID
POLITICAL CAMPAIGN AGAINST
SPECIFIC REPORTERS, THAT SEEMS
UNUSUAL.
>> YEAH, THAT WAS A NEW ANGLE
LAST NIGHT IN GRAND RAPIDS.
YOU KNOW, THAT WAS A
LOLLAPALOOZA OF A SPEECH.
THE PRESIDENT WENT ALMOST TWO
HOURS.
I THINK FIDEL CASTRO ONCE WENT
FIVE HOURS.
NOW, WHEN I TELL HIM THAT CASTRO
WENT FIVE HOURS, HE'LL GO, I CAN
DO THAT AND MIGHT DO IT.
TO ATTACK THE PRESS, I DO NOT
KNOW, JOHN, WHO THE DEMOCRATIC
NOMINEE IS GOING TO BE NEXT
YEAR.
IT WON'T BE ME, IT WON'T BE A
REPORTER.
TO RUN AGAINST US HE'S GOT TO
RUN AGAINST A REAL, LIVE PERSON
WHO WANTS TO BE PRESIDENT.
AND THE ISSUES ARE GOING TO BE
IMPORTANT.
HE GIVES US, HE GIVES THEM
HEALTH CARE.
HE SAYS LET'S RUN ON HEALTH
CARE.
PLEASE, PLEASE, COME AHEAD.
LET'S DO THAT.
LET'S RUN ON CRUELTY TO CHILDREN
HERE IN THE UNITED STATES.
LOOK AT HIS BUDGET.
LET'S TAKE MONEY AWAY FROM THE
SPECIAL OLYMPICS.
WELL, MS. DeVOS HAD TO BACKTRACK
ON THAT WHEN THE PRESSURE GOT
TOO HARD.
LET'S LOOK AT HIS RECORD.
HE'S RUNNING, NOT THE PRESS.
AND THE FACTS WILL BE OUT.
>> DO YOU FEEL, THOUGH, THAT THE
REPEATED ATTACKS, THAT IT COULD
BE POLITICALLY EFFECTIVE?
>> IT WILL BE POLITICALLY
EFFECTIVE WITH HIS BASE.
HE'S GOT 31%, 32%, HARDCORE.
HE CAN DO ANYTHING, AS HE SAYS,
SHOOT SOMEBODY IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE DAY, WOULDN'T LOSE A SINGLE
ONE OF THEIR VOTES.
BUT THEY'RE NOT THE MAJORITY IN
THIS COUNTRY.
THEY'RE NEVER GOING TO BE THE
MAJORITY, I DON'T BELIEVE.
I DID AN INTERVIEW WITH HIM IN
1990.
AN INTERVIEW ABOUT HIS BUSINESS.
HIS BUSINESS WAS FAILING BUT HE
BLEW A LOT OF SMOKE.
DURING THE COURSE OF THE
INTERVIEW HE CALLED ME RUDE, HE
CALLED ME IGNORANT.
I'M NOT THAT SMART.
HE CALLED ME OUT TO GET HIM.
SO I'M ONE OF THE PIONEERS OF
THE DONALD J. TRUMP ATTACK
MACHINE.
IT DIDN'T HURT ME.
I JUST WENT ON.
BY THE WAY, I WAS NOT OUT TO GET
HIM AT THAT TIME.
AND I'M NOT OUT TO GET HIM NOW.
HE WANTS TO RUN ON ALL OF THIS
JUNK.
I THINK HIS OPPONENT OUGHT TO
RUN ON THE ISSUES THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE REALLY APPARENTLY CARE
ABOUT.
LAST NOVEMBER, THEY WEIGHED IN,
MR. PRESIDENT.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THAT?
DID YOU WIN THAT?
YES, ON ELECTION NIGHT YOU SAID
IT WAS ALMOST A TOTAL VICTORY.
ONCE AGAIN, DOES HE REALLY KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> LET ME ASK YOU THIS, SAM.
YOU COVERED MANY ADMINISTRATIONS
AND MANY PRESIDENTS.
LAST NIGHT SPEAKING BEFORE THIS
CROWD, THE PRESIDENT SAID, AND I
QUOTE, RIDICULOUS --.
HE WAS TALKING ABOUT THINGS THAT
CONGRESS WAS SAYING ABOUT HIM
AND HE USED THOSE WORDS.
ARE THOSE WORDS IN YOUR MIND
THAT THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES SHOULD BE USING?
HE'S USED THEM BEFORE.
AND WHAT'S THE IMPACT OF THAT
OVER TIME?
>> I THINK THE IMPACT IS TO TURN
A LOT OF PEOPLE OFF.
MAYBE NOT HIS BASE.
THEY MAKE EXCUSES FOR HIM.
WELL, HE WAS JUST TRYING TO MAKE
A POINT.
IT WAS LOCKER ROOM TALK, WE ALL
DO THAT.
NO, WE DON'T ALL DO THAT.
AND IF WE DO IT, WE DO IT
PRIVATELY AND JUST WITH OUR
GENTLEMAN FRIENDS.
HAVE I USED THAT WORD YOU JUST
USED?
SURE, I HAVE.
NOT ON TELEVISION, NOT IN
PUBLIC, NOT TO PEOPLE IF I DO A
TALK ONCE IN A WHILE.
THIS IS A PRESIDENT WHO DOES NOT
CONFORM TO ANY RULES AND NORMS
OF CIVILITY, ANY RULES AND NORMS
OF BEHAVIOR THAT I THINK MOST
AMERICANS WANT TO SEE, WHETHER
THEY WANT TO SEE IT IN THEIR
HOUSE OF WORSHIP, WHETHER THEY
WANT TO SEE IT IN THEIR SCHOOLS,
WHETHER THEY WANT TO SEE IT IN
THEIR CLUBS, WHETHER THEY WANT
TO SEE IT IN THEIR SOCIAL LIFE.
HE DOESN'T CARE.
I THINK AMERICANS CARE.
I THINK YOU'LL FIND THAT OUT.
BUT I COULD BE WRONG.
>> SAM DONALDSON, ONE OF MY
FAVORITE, MY ABSOLUTE FAVORITE
FORMER ABC NEWS REPORTERS, THANK
YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING WITH US.
>> JOHN, I'VE SAID IT BEFORE,
YOU'RE TOO EASILY PLEASED.
>> I APPRECIATE IT, SAM.
AS I SAID, YOU'RE MY FAVORITE.
>>> NOW, TO ONE OF MY TOP 10 OR
15 FAVORITE FORMER ABC NEWS
REPORTERS, CHRIS CUOMO.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT'S
COMING UP AT THE TOP OF THE
HOUR.
>> EASY, HE WAS MY MENTOR.
I DID A SHOW WITH SAM.
>> HE WAS MY FAVORITE.
>> HE TAUGHT ME A LOT OF MY
TACTICS.
>> HE WAS MY FAVORITE.
YOU'RE ONE OF MY TOP TEN.
YOU'RE UP THERE.
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, THAT'S
OKAY.
LET ME TELL YOU, THIS IS THE
FIRST TIME I'VE EVER SAID THIS.
I THINK SAM IS WRONG.
ONE, HE IS MAYBE ONE OF THE
FIRST VICTIMS OF THE TRUMP PR
MACHINE.
I DON'T THINK SO.
HE WROTE A LETTER WHEN CHRIS AND
I WERE INVESTIGATING HIS NET
WORTH WHERE HE DAMNED ME BACK TO
THE WOMB.
HE WAS GOING TO SUE ME, ALL OF
ABC, ALL OF DISNEY, AND MY
PARENTS.
DAMNING ME BACK TO THE WOMB,
LITERALLY.
EVEN THOUGH IT WAS WRITTEN BY
HIS LAWYER, WE THEORIZED THAT HE
NOT ONLY WROTE IT OR HAD A HAND
IN IT BUT DICTATED IT BECAUSE IT
SOUNDED JUST LIKE HIM.
AND FOR THE COARSE LANGUAGE, HE
DOES IT BECAUSE IT WORKS FOR
HIM.
SAM IS THERE ON THE SCREEN.
I LOVE YOU, YOU LOOK AS GOOD AS
EVER AND YOUR POINTS ARE AS
SALIENT AS EVER.
BUT I BELIEVE HIS COARSENESS IS
A DEVICE.
>> SAM, CUOMO SAYS YOU'RE WRONG.
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO HIM?
>> I GOT ATTACKED PERSONALLY ON
CAMERA BY HIM.
YOU GOT A LETTER?
COME ON, CHRIS.
YOU KNOW BETTER THAN THAT.
I'M THE WINNER, I'M THE BIG ONE.
OH, GOSH, IT'S INFECTIOUS, ISN'T
IT?
>> HE TOLD ME THE REASON HE GETS
AUDITED SO MUCH BY THE IRS IS
BECAUSE HE'S SUCH A DEVOUT
CHRISTIAN.
>> TRUMP?
>> YEAH, HE TOLD ME THAT DURING
A DEBATE.
MY POINT IS THIS.
HE SAYS OUTLANDISH THINGS AND IT
MAKES PEOPLE THINK, SEE, HE'S
ONE OF US.
HE'S NOT ONE OF THEM, HE'S NOT A
POLITICIAN, HE'S NOT AN ELITE.
HE TALKS LIKE US, HE MAKES
POINTS LIKE WE DO, HE'S ABOUT
US.
I THINK IT WORKS TO HIS
ADVANTAGE.
WE'LL SEE HOW IT PLAYS OUT, BUT
THAT'S MY SENSE.
>> SAM DONALDSON, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
CHRIS AND I COLLECTIVELY, YOU
ARE OUR FAVORITE.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
CHRIS, WE LOOK FORWARD TO YOUR
SHOW IN ABOUT 11 MINUTES.
>>> YESTERDAY'S STUNNING
REVERSAL ON SPECIAL OLYMPIC
FUNDING WAS JUST THE LATEST
EXAMPLE OF PRESIDENT TRUMP
UNDERCUTTING A MEMBER OF HIS
WE'LL SPEAK WITH DAVID GERGEN
WHO WORKED FOR FOUR PRESIDENTS
ABOUT THIS UNUSUAL PATTERN,
NEXT. vo■o■o■
Run with us
on a John Deere
1 Series tractor.
should be as easy as...
What about this?
Changing your plans.
Yeah.
Run with us.
Search "John Deere 1 Series"
for more.
[farmers bell]
Yeah.
(Driver)
Relax, it's just a bug.
That's not a bug,
that's not a bug!
(Burke)
Hit and Drone.
we've seen a thing or two.7w ae
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
YEAH!
OHH
We hide hotel names,
YEAH!
so you can find four star
hotels at two rices.
[Dophin making]
E-E-■
I thought I married an Italian.
Did the AncestryDNA to
find out I'm only 16% Italian.
So I went onto Ancestry,
Soon learned that one of our
ancestors was Eastern European.
This is my ancestor
who I didn't know about.
Each day Justin
chooses to walk.
Heit all with
Dr. Scholl's.
Only Dr. Scholl's has
Massaging Gel Insoles
that provide
all-day comfort.
To keep him feeling
more energized.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to Move.
With Expedia,
I saved when I added
a hotel to our flight.
So even when
she grows up,
Unlock savings
when you add
select hotels to your
existing trip.
Only with Expedia.
I have a vision
correction number,
But I'm more than a number.
When I'm not teaching,
I'm taking steep grades
and tight corners.
My Essilor lenses offer more
than vision correction
with three innovative
technologies
For my ultimate in vision
And Protection
Together in a single lens:
The Essilor Ultimate
Lens Package.
So, I can do more
of what I love!
Buy two pairs of
Essilor's best lenses
and get a $100 back instantly.
See more. Do more. Essilor
>>> EDUCATION SECRETARY BETSY
DeVOS SPENT THIS WEEK GETTING
GRILLED BY CONGRESSIONAL
DEMOCRATS IN HEARINGS OVER THE
PROPOSAL TO ELIMINATE FEDERAL
FUNDING FOR THE SPECIAL
OLYMPICS.
IT WAS A TOUGH SELL TO
LAWMAKERS.
THEN SHE HAD TO FACE THE PRESS,
WHICH LED TO AWKWARD MOMENTS
LIKE THIS ONE YOU'RE SEEING
RIGHT HERE.
BUT DeVOS STOOD BY HER PROPOSAL
TO CUT NEARLY $18 MILLION IN
FUNDING TO THE PROGRAM.
THEN YESTERDAY AFTERNOON, A
TOTAL REVERSAL.
PRESIDENT TRUMP APPARENTLY
UNBEKNOWNST TO BETSY DeVOS
ANNOUNCED THAT THE MONEY WON'T
BE CUT AFTER ALL.
>> I'VE BEEN TO THE SPECIAL
OLYMPICS, I THINK IT'S
INCREDIBLE.
I JUST AUTHORIZED A FUNDING.
I HEARD ABOUT IT THIS MORNING.
I HAVE OVERRIDDEN MY PEOPLE.
WE'RE FUNDING THE SPECIAL
OLYMPICS.
>> SO AS RANDI KAYE REPORTS,
THIS IS NOT THE FIRST OR THE
SECOND TIME THAT THE PRESIDENT
HAS THROWN ONE OF HIS CABINET
MEMBERS UNDER THE BUS.
>> THE PRESIDENT CAN'T UNDERCUT
HIS OWN CABINET.
THE PRES THE LEADER OF
THE CABINET. orter: DESPITE WHA
PRESS SECRETARY SAYS, PRESIDENT
DONALD TRUMP DOES EXACTLY THAT,
UNDERCUTS NOT JUST HIS CABINET
BUT MANY ON HIS WHITE HOUSE
STAFF, AGAIN AND AGAIN.
DURING THE TRAVEL BAN --
>> FIRST OF ALL, IT'S NOT A
TRAVEL BAN.
WHEN WE USE WORDS LIKE TRAVEL
BAN THAT, MISREPRESENTS WHAT IT
IS.
>> Reporter: JUST A FEW DAYS
LATER, THE PRESIDENT HIMSELF
STILL CALLING IT A BAN, TWEETING
WHAT IS OUR COUNTRY COMING TO
WHEN A JUDGE CAN HALT A HOMELAND
SECURITY TRAVEL BAN?T AGAIN AFT
THEN FBI DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY.
THE WHITE HOUSE STAFF HAS ONE
NARRATIVE.
>> HE ACTED DECISIVELY TODAY.
HE TOOK THE RECOMMENDATION OF T■
>> Reporter: A DEPUTY ATTORNEY■á
GE■o2 LIKE COMEY'S LING OF THE
E-MAIL INVESTIGATION.
BUT IN THIS BOMBSHELL INTERVIEW
WITH NBC, THE PRESIDENT SAYS
COMEY WAS FIRED BECAUSE OF THE
RUSSIA INVESTIGATION.
>> IN FACT WHEN I DECIDED TO
JUST DO IT, I SAID TO MYSELF, I
SAID, YOU KNOW, THIS RUSSIA
THING WITH TRUMP AND RUSSIA IS A
MADE-UP STORY.
>> Reporter: RUSSIA WAS THE
REASON TRUMP UNDERCUT HIS
DIRECTOR OF NATIONAL
INTELLIGENCE TOO, CASTING DOUBT
ON DAN COATS' WARNING ABOUT
RUSSIAN INTERFERENCE.
AFTER TRUMP MET WITH PUTIN IN
HELSINKI, HE WAS ASKED WHOM HE
BELIEVED REGARDING RUSSIAN
MEDDLING IN THE 2016 ELECTION.
TRUMP SAID THIS.
>> MY PEOPLE CAME TO ME, DAN
COATS CAME TO ME AND SOME
OTHERS.
THEY SAID THEY THINK IT'S
RUSSIA.
I HAVE PRESIDENT PUTIN.
HE JUST SAID IT'S NOT RUSSIA.
I HAVE GREAT CONFIDENCE IN MY
INTELLIGENCE PEOPLE, BUT I WILL
TELL YOU THAT PRESIDENT PUTIN
WAS EXTREMELY STRONG AND
POWERFUL IN HIS DENIAL TODAY.
>> Reporter: AND WHAT ABOUT
REPORTS THAT THE PRESIDENT HAD
REVEALED HIGHLY CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION TO RUSSIAN OFFICIALS
IN THE OVAL OFFICE?
TEAM TRUMP REFUTED THAT.
HIS NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISOR AT
THE TIME QUICK TO CALL THE
REPORT FALSE.
>> AT NO TIME WERE INTELLIGENCE
SOURCES OR METHODS DISCUSSED.
I WAS IN THE ROOM, IT DIDN'T
HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: CUE THE PRESIDENT
THE NEXT MORNING, SEEMING TO
CONTRADICT HIS NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISOR.
TWEETING, AS PRESIDENT, I WANTED
TO SHARE WITH RUSSIA AT AN
OPENLY SCHEDULED WHITE HOUSE
MEETING WHICH I HAVE THE
ABSOLUTE RIGHT TO DO.
FACTS PERTAINING TO TERRORISM
AND AIRLINE FLIGHT SAFETY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP UNDERCUT HIS
FORMER SECRETARY OF STATE, REX
TILLERSON, TOO.
WHILE TILLERSON WAS ON A
DIPLOMATIC TRIP TO BEIJING,
HOPING TO MAKE A DEAL ON NORTH
KOREA.
TRUMP TWEETING HE'S WASTING HIS
TIME TRYING TO NEGOTIATE WITH
LITTLE ROCKET MAN.
MORE RECENTLY ON THE LOOMING
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN, VICE
PRESIDENT MIKE PENCE WAS THE T■0
AFTER HIS OFFICE CHARACTERIZED
THE MEETINGS HE HAD WITH AIDES
TO TOP DEMOCRATS AS PRODUCTIVE,
TRUMP THREW WATER ON THAT
TWEETING VP MIKE PENCE JUST LEFT
THE WHITE HOUSE.
NOT MUCH HEADWAY MADE TODAY.
RANDI KAYE, CNN, NEW YORK.
>>> DAVID GERGEN HAS ADVISED
FOUR PRESIDENTS.
HE'S ALSO A CNN SENIOR POLITICAL
ANALYST.
DAVID, WHEN YOU SEE THIS, THIS
PUBLIC REALLY FLOGGING AND
UNDERCUTTING OF CABINET MEMBERS
AND WHITE HOUSE STAFF, WHAT DOES
IT TELL YOU?
>> IT TELLS ME THAT THIS
PRESIDENT, HIS NARCISSISM KNOWS
NO BOUNDS.
LISTEN, LEADERSHIP 101 TEACHES
YOU THAT IF YOU'RE GOING TO LEAD
A GROUP OF PEOPLE, THAT YOU WANT
THEM TO BE LOYAL TO YOU.
BUT IT'S ALSO IMPORTANT THAT
LOYALTY RUNS BOTH WAYS.
IN THIS CASE THE PRESIDENT
CONTINUALLY DISMISSES OTHERS
BECAUSE HE WANTS TO BE THE
CENTER OF ATTENTION.
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING MORE GOING
ON HERE I MIGHT SUGGEST, JOHN.
THAT IS I THINK COMING OUT OF
THE MUELLER REPORT AND WHAT HE
SEES AS COMPLETE EXONERATION,
HE'S GOT A NEW SWAGGER ABOUT HIM
THESE LAST FEW DAYS.
SO WHAT HAS HE DONE?
HE'S OVERRIDDEN BETSY DeVOS, ONE
OF THE MOST LOYAL MEMBERS OF HIS
CABINET.
HE'S THROWN A MONKEY WRENCH INTO
THE HEALTH CARE ISSUE IN SUCH A
WAY THAT HIS OWN REPUBLICANS ARE
RUNNING SCARED FROM IT.
TAKE MITCH McCONNELL, FOR
EXAMPLE.
HE'S ALSO NOW DECLARED THAT
HE'LL CLOSE THE BORDER WITH
MEXICO.
THOSE ARE ALL ACTS OF SOMEONE
WHO REALLY HAS A SENSE OF I'M IN
CHARGE HERE, I'M COMPLETELY IN
CHARGE.
I'M GOING TO DO WHAT I WANT, I
DON'T GIVE A DARN WHAT OTHER
PEOPLE THINK.
AND THERE'S A CERTAIN ARROGANCE
ABOUT THIS THAT I THINK IS GOING
TO IN THE LONG RUN COST HIM A
LOT.
>> THIS IS A HUBRIS WE'VE SEEN
THIS WEEK.
I'M NOT TOTALLY SURE THAT WE SEE
DIFFERENT ACTIONS FROM THE
PRESIDENT IN THE WAKE OF THAT
HUBRIS BECAUSE THE SPLITS AND
THE UNDERCUTTING OF THE CABINET
MEMBERS IS SOMETHING WE'VE SEEN
BEFORE.
THERE ARE THOSE THAT WONDER,
DAVID, IF WHETHER OR NOT HE
TREATS IT AS SORT OF A PUBLIC
FLOAT.
HE DOESN'T CARE SPLITTING WITH
HIS OWN ADMINISTRATION IF HE
DOESN'T SEE THE APPROVAL FOR
SOME OF THE POLICIES THAT HE
WANTS TO OUT THERE.
>> NO, AND I THINK THAT'S RIGHT.
I THINK HE VALUES SENDING A
MESSAGE TO HIS BASE THAT HE'S
HIS OWN INDEPENDENT GUY.
HE'S NOT ONLY NOT BEHOLDEN TO
DEMOCRATS, BUT HE'S NOT BEHOLDEN
TO ANYBODY ELSE IN HIS OWN
PARTY, IN HIS OWN WHITE HOUSE.
AND THAT'S THE REASON HE'S GOT
THIS HUGE AMOUNT OF TURNOVER.
I THINK IF YOU TAKE ALL FOUR
PRESIDENTS I WORKED FOR
COMBINED, I DON'T THINK THERE
WAS AS MUCH TURNOVER AS THERE
HAS BEEN IN THIS WHITE HOUSE IN
THE LAST COUPLE OF YEARS.
>> THE THING IS, THOUGH, THERE'S
SOMETHING DISINGENUOUS ABOUT IT.
THIS WAS A TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
BUDGET THAT BETSY DeVOS WAS
DEFENDING ON CAPITOL HILL.
>> YES, I'M SO GLAD YOU RAISE
THAT POINT, THANK YOU.
YES.
WHAT THAT MEANS IS THAT BUDGET
WENT THROUGH THE OFFICE OF
MANAGEMENT AND BUDGET WHERE
MULVANEY STILL HAS A HUGE AMOUNT
OF POWER.
THEN IT WENT THROUGH THE WEST
WING AND HAD TO BE APPROVED BITE
PRESIDENT.
THEY HAD TO RED FLAG ANYTHING IN
THERE THAT WAS CONTROVERSIAL TO
GET IT BY THE PRESIDENT.
THEN IT WAS PUBLISHED AND THEN,
AHA, I ONLY LEARNED ABOUT IT
FIVE MINUTES AGO AND I'M
COMPLETELY OVERRIDING MY
SECRETARY BE DAMNED.
>> YEAH, IT REALLY JUST DOESN'T
PASS THE SMELL TEST THAT IT
DIDN'T HAVE HIS STAMP OF
APPROVAL GOING IN.
CERTAINLY SOMEONE WITHIN THE
WHITE HOUSE KNEW ABOUT IT THE
WHOLE TIME.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> DAVID GERGEN, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH FOR BEING WITH US.
THANK YOU FOR HELPING US
UNDERSTAND, WHICH MAY NOT BE
UNDERSTANDABLE SOMETIMES.
REALLY APPRECIATE IT.