>> WHAT'S THE DREAM TEAM LOOKING
UP?
>> CAKE.
>> SEEING OUR STUDENTS REALLY
COME INTO THE.
GO TO CNN HEROS.COM.
CNNHEROS.COM.
THANKS FOR BEING WITH ME ON THIS
FRIDAY AFTERNOON.
STAY RIGHT HERE.
THE LEAD STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>>> BREAKING NEWS, NEW DETAILS
ON PLANS TO RELEASE THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S REDACTED REPORT TO
CONGRESS.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL SAYS THE
HANDS ON IT FIRST. GETTING HIS■z
APPROVED BY THE TRUMP WHITE
HOUSE THAT CRITICS FEAR COULD  .
>>> WELCOME TO THE LEAD.
I'M IN FOR JAKE.
BREAKING NEWS IN OUR POLITICS
LEAD.
THE MUELLER REPORT WILL BE READY
FOR RELEASE BY MID-APRIL AND
MAYBE EVEN SOONER.
BARR SAID HIS TEAM ALONG WITH
SPECIAL COUNSEL ARE MAKING
REDACTIONS RIGHT NOW.
WE ARE ALSO LEARNING THE REPORT
IS NEARLY 400 PAGES LONG NOT
COUNTING EXHIBITS.
LAURA JOINING ME LIVE NOW.
TELL US WHAT WE ARE LEARNING.
>> THE ATTORNEY GENERAL TRYING
TO TAKE THE ISSUE OF EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE OFF THE TABLE.
THERE HAVE BEEN SOME SPECULATION
AND DEBATE ABOUT WHETHER THE
WHITE HOUSE WOULD TRY TO SHIELD
PARTS OF THIS REPORT USING THE
GROUNDS OF DPEKTIVE PRIVILEGE.
BILL BARR SAYING NOT SO.
IN HIS LETTER TO CONGRESS HE
SAYS ALTHOUGH THE PRESIDENT
WOULD HAVE THE RIGHT TO EXERT
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE HE HAS
STATED PUBLICLY HE INTENDS TO
DEFER TO ME.
ACCORDINGLY THERE WILL BE NO
PLANS TO SUBMIT THE REPORT TO
THE WHITE HOUSE.
HE GOES ONTO EXPLAIN THE REPORT
IS BEING REDACTED AS WELL AS
ONGOING INVESTIGATIONS ALSO TO
PROTECT THE PERIPHERAL RIGHTS OF
THIRD PARTIES.
SORT OF A CURIOUS LINE THERE.
HE ALSO TRIES TO DEFEND HIMSELF
OVER THE LAST WEEK THAT HE TOOK
400 PAGES AND CONDENSED THEM
DOWN SAYING THAT'S NOT REALLY
FAIR.
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE A SUMMARY
OF PRINCIPLE CONCLUSIONS AND
EVERYONE WILL BE ABLE TO READ IT
ON THEIR OWN.
>> IS THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
EXPECTED TO TESTIFY ABOUT THE
MUELLER REPORT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
HE REALIZES THE PUBLIC INTEREST
AND WHAT HE HAS TO SAY ABOUT IT
IS VERY STRONG.
HE IS OFFERING TWO DATES IN THIS
NEW LETTER TO CONGRESS MAY 1st
AND MAY SECOND.
ALMOST 400 PAGES WE ARE TOLD
ABOUT THIS REPORT.
IT SEEMS AS THOUGH ATTORNEY
GENERAL BARR IS TRYING TO BE
TRANSPARENT AS POSSIBLE HERE AT
LEAST AT THIS MOMENT IN TIME.
I WOULD ASK ALL OF YOU IF THE
TIMING MATTERS FOR THIS
TRANSPARENCY AND SORT OF WHAT
THE EFFECT IS OF THAT HAVING HAD
THIS SUMMARY OUT ALREADY.
>> I THINK IT DOES.
THERE ARE LONG REDACTIONS.
IF IT WERE ON THE DEMOCRATIC
SIDE IT WOULD NOT TAKE THIS
LONG.
SO I THINK THAT WE HAVE TO BE
MINDFUL OF THAT.
SHE NOT ONE OF THE CRITICISMS OF
HIM IS SHE A BIAS NARRATOR.
HE DEFENDED THE FIRING OF COMEY
WHEN HE WAS TRYING OUT FOR THE
JOB.
IT GIVES THEM A LOT OF
BANDWIDTH.
THEY WILL BE SEEING HOW HE USES
THE CATEGORIES OF REDACTION.
>> CAN HE HIT THE MARKET OF
TRANSPARENCY AT THIS POINT IN
TIME?
>> WHY NOT?
AT THE END OF THE DAY IT DUOES
TAKE A LITTLE BIT OF TIME.
ALL MEMBERS WOULD ACTUALLY LIKE
TO SEE AS MUCH OF THIS AS
POSSIBLE WHEN ALL DEMOCRATS ARE
UNIFIED IN SAYING MORE
TRANSPARENCY MAKES IT PUBLIC.
I UNDERSTAND IT'S NOT AT A LEVEL
DEMOCRATS WOULD LIKE.
THEY HAVE BEEN CALLING FOR THIS
BEFORE THE REPORT WAS INITIALLY
RELEASED.
I THINK IT'S NOT ON THE
TIMETABLE.
>> THE REDACTIONS, THE SUMMARY
ALLOWING THE NARRATIVE TO KIND
OF BE --
>> IT IS TO VERY MUCH.
>> I FEEL LIKE FOCUSING IS SOME
WHAT KIND OF SILLY.
IT IS AN INVESTIGATIVE MATTER.
IT IS LESS IMPORTANT TO ME I
THINK FOR 400 PAGES TO TAKE THE
TIME TO MAKE SURE IT'S NOT
JEOPARDIZING NATIONAL SECURITY
THAT SHOULDN'T BE JEOPARDIZED.
I THINK IT'S PERFECTLY FAIR.
THIS IDEA THAT BARR WILL PUT OUT
A SUMMARY IS CRAZY.
HIS FOLKS ARE NOT GOING TO ALLOW
A FALSE NARRATIVE.
>> BUT HE MADE A CONCLUSION.
HE GOT OUT OF HAVING TO TESTIFY.
WHEN WE ARE TALKING ABOUT WE
HAVE SEEN ROUGHLY 500100 WORDS
YESTERDAY IT WAS 300 AND NOW WE
THINK IT IS ABOUT 400 PAGES.
I ALSO HAVE TO BELIEVE THEY WANT
TO SEE ALL OF THE INFORMATION
THEY WANT CONGRESS TO CONTINUE
TO PRESS.
THE NARRATIVE DOES MATTER.
I WILL GIVE YOU THE SUMMARY
BEFORE THE END OF THE WEEKEND.
WE WERE ALL SITTING HERE WAITING
FOR THAT SUMMARY.
AGAIN, 50 WORDS OUT OF NOW 500
P
PAGES WE LEARNED.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT THE REST OF
PARAGRAPH SAID AROUND WHY WAS IT
THAT BOB MUELLER.
>> AND IN MID-APRIL WE WILL
KNOW.
>> NO.
IN MID-APRIL WE WILL STILL SEE
SOME VERSION OF WHAT BAR DECIDES
TO SHOW US.
>> RIGHT.
IT HAS A LOT OF DISCRETION.
WE ALREADY FLOW SENATOR GRAM AND
I'M SURE DEMOCRATS WILL GO UP.
ANY OF THESE WILL BE IN FULL
PUBLIC VIEWING.
THIS SPAN ABOUT HOW OF COURSE HE
IS GOING TO TELL US EVERYTHING
WE NEED TO KNOW.
>> IS THIS A DEEP THROAT TYPE OF
SITUATION?
THE.
>> I'M SUGGESTING THERE ARE
PARTS WE MAY NOT SEE FOR QUITE
SOME TIME.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THAT.
WE'LL HAVE THE MOST OPPORTUNITY
TO HAVE AND EVERYONE WANTS IT TO
BE RELEASED AND IT WILL.
THERE WHAT I HAVE HEARD WE KNOW
THERE WERE SOME CONVERSATIONS
BETWEEN DOJ ABD AND MUELLER
SEVERAL WEEKS AGO.
SOME SUGGESTED THAT'S WHY HE HAD
IT ABOUT JOHN McCAIN.
>> WHILE THERE MAY BE THINGS
THAT DON'T RISE TO THE LEGAL
LEVEL THERE COULD BE UNSAVOR RI
THINGS IN THERE THAT DO NOT PLAY
WELL FOR THE PRESIDENT.
SHE NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO MAKE
AN ARGUMENT ABOUT EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE.
THAT IS KEY ISN'T IT?
>> YES.
IT SOUNDS LIKE IT IS.
HOWEVER ATTORNEY GENERAL BAR,
IT'S HIS HAND PICKED PERSON AS
IT WORKS ALWAYS FOR ATTORNEY
GENERAL.
HE HAS SHOWN HIMSELF TO BE A
DEFENDER OF DONALD TRUMP'S
ACTIONS INCLUDING FIRING COMEY
AT THE TIME WRITING A 19 PAGE
MEMO.
>> AND THAT IS A WAY OF
SCRUBBING EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE?
>> HE MADE A DECISION THAT
MUELLER DIDN'T DECIDE IN THE
M
MEMO HE RELEASED.
THAT'S WHY I'M CONCERNED AND
PEOPLE SHOULD BE CONCERNED ABOUT
HIS CATEGORIES OF REDACTIONS.
IT LEAVES HIM ON ENORMOUS AMOUNT
OF REDACTION.
>> I WOULD SAY TO COMEY, I THINK
THEY ARE UNIFIED IN NOT LIKING
THE MAN.
ZBLI ALSO ABSOLUTELY THE
PRESIDENT'S PER OGTIVE TO FIRE
ANY MEMBER OF HIS CABINET.
I UNDERSTAND THE CIRCUMSTANCES
WERE NOT WHAT ONE WOULD NORMALLY
EXPECT.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT HE WAS
ARGUING.
>> HE WAS NOT SAYING THIS IS ALL
A GREAT WAY DONALD TRUMP FIRED
HIM.
HE WAS SAYING HE HAS THE
AUTHORITY TO DO THAT.
>> I THINK IF HE WERE FIRING THE
EPA ADMINISTRATOR THAT IS ONE
THING.
HE IS THREATENING TO SHUT DOWN
THE SOUTHERN BORDER.
THE UNITED STATES ACCUSED OF
SHARING COME OF AMERICA'S TOP
NUCLEAR SECRETS WITH THE SAME
COUNTRY ACCUSEDO OF KILLING A
U.S. RESIDENT AND WASHINGTON
POST JOURNALIST.
With moderate
to severe Crohn's disease,
I was there, jt not
always where I needed to be.
Is she alright?
I hope so.
So I talked to my doctor
about HUMIRA.
I learned HUMIRA is for people
who still have symptoms
of Crohn's disease
after trying other mications.
And the majority
of people on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom relief
and many achieved remission
in as little as 4 weeks.
HU■■■■■&ability
to fight infections,
■■,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, happen,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
■ou
've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Be there for you, and them.
Ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA,
remission is possible.
♪ ♪ ♪
OUR NEW, HOT, FRESH BREAKFAST
WILL GET YOU THE READIEST.
(BUZZER SOUND)
HOLIDAY INN EXPRESS.
BE THE READIEST.
(baby crying)
♪ Just hold on, I'm comin' ♪
♪ Hold on, I'm comin' ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ Don't you worry, I'm comin' ♪
♪ Here I come ♪
Nothing comes easily.
That's what happens in golf
and in life.
I'm very fortunate
I can lean on people,
and that for me
is what teamwork
is all about.
You can't do everything
yourself.
You need someone to guide you
and help you make those tough
decisions,
that's Morgan Stanley.
They're industry leaders,
but the most important thing is
they want to do it
the right way.
I'm really excited to be part of
the Morgan Stanley team.
I'm Justin Rose.
are Morgan Stanley.
Every day at Marco's,
get 2 Medium,
1-Topping Pizzas
for 99 each.
■■■■■■■■■■
Because it takes two...
to make a great everyday
value.
Every store.
Every day.
The Italian Way.
Hello Primo.
So, JARDIANCE asks...
When it comes to
type 2 diabetes,
are you thinking about
your heart?
Well, I'm managing my A1C,
so I should be all set.
Right.
Actually, you're still at risk
for a fatal heart attack
or stroke.
Even if I'm taking
heart medicine,
like statins or blood thinners?
Yep!
That's why I asked my doctor
what else I could do...
she told me about JARDIANCE.
That's right.
JARDIANCE significantly reduces
the risk of dying
from a cardiovascular event
for adults who have
type 2 diabetes
and known heart disease.
That's why the American Diabetes
Association recommends
the active ingredient
in JARDIANCE.
And it lowers A1C?
Yeah- with diet and exercise.
JARDIANCE can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration,
genital yeast or
urinary tract infections,
Ketoacidosis is a serious
side effect
that may be fatal.
A rare, but life-threatening,
bacterial infection
in the skin of the perineum
could occur.
Stop taking JARDIANCE
and call your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of this bacterial infection,
ketoacidosis,
or an allergic reaction.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Taking JARDIANCE
with a sulfonylurea
or insulin may cause
low gar.
So, what do you think?
Now I feel I can do more
to go beyond lowering A1C.
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE
today.
>>> McMAN IS A TRUMP CABINET
ORIGINAL AND HEADED TO THE
PRESIDENT'S OUTSIDE POLITICAL
GROUP.
AS ABBY PHILLIPS REPORTS AS ONE
GETS READY ANOTHER IS TRYING TO
GRIN AND BEAR I
>> AFTER A WEEK OF PUBLICLY AND
PRIVATELY DISAGREEING WITH
SEVERAL CABINET MEMBERS.
>> I HAVE OVERRIDDEN MY PEOPLE.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS LOSING ONE
OF THE FEW MEMBER OF HIS TEAM HE
NEVER PUBLICLY DISAGREED WITH.
SMALL BUSINESS ADMINISTRATOR WHO
ONCE RAN WORLD WRESTLING
ENTERTAINMENT IS LEAVING TO TAKE
A SENIOR ROLE AT AMERICA FIRST,
AN OUTSIDE POLITICAL GROUP THAT
SUPPORTS THE PRESIDENT.
THIS IS AFTER THE PRESIDENT'S
PUBLIC SPLIT WITH ANOTHER MEMBE
SECRETARY AND HER PLANS DESCRIBE
FEDERAL FUNDING FOR THE SPECIAL
OLYMPICS.
>> I JUST TOLD MY PEOPLE I WANT
TO FUND THE SPECIAL OLYMPICS.
WITH THE CLEARING CLOUD OF THE
MUELLER INFORMATION PRESIDENT
TRUMP GEARING UP FOR A FIGHT
WITH DEMOCRATS OVER HEALTH CARE.
GROUP OF REPUBLICANS INCLUDE
RICK SCOTT WORKING ON AN
ALTERNATIVE.
THE PRESIDENT RENEWING HIS FIGHT
FOR A BORDER■ WALL.
VO SHUT DOWN AS EARLY AS
NEXT WEEK AND ADMITTING SHUTTING
DOWN THE BORDER COULD T
>> ALL TRADE.
MEXICO IS MAKING■■■■■■BSOLUTELY
FORTUNE.
■■■■■■■■■■ IT CLOSE FAR LONG
TIME.
I'M NOT PLAYING GAMES. H THIS T
CLOSEI■ BORDER BEFORE.■■
HE NEVER ACTUALLY DONE IT IN
PART BECAUSE LOTS OF PEOPLE HERE
IN WASHINGTON IN HIS
ADMINISTRATION INCLUDING MANY
LAWMAKERS HAVE TOLD HIM THAT
DOING THAT COULD CAUSE ECONOMIC
DAMAGE.
IT IS TO DEAL WITH AN INFLUX OF
IMGRANLTS WHO ARE CROSSING
ILLEGALLY.
AS OF RIGHT NOW THEY HAVE NOT
YET CLOSED ANY PARTS OF THE
BORDER.
>> I ASKED THE DEPUTY DIRECTOR
TODAY.
HE COMPLETELY SIDESTEPPED THE
QUESTION.
THAT MIGHT TELL YOU WHAT THEY DO
OR DON'T WANT.
THANK YOU.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT LINDA McMANN
OVER TO THIS PACK.
IS THIS A SMART MOVE FOR HER?
IT IS SORT OF A LANDING PLACE IS
A PRETTY COMMON STEP FOR THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION.
I DON'T THINK IT RAISES ANY KIND
OF UNUSUAL CONCERN.
IT'S NOT AS THOUGH SHE IS
LEVERING UNDER ANY CLOUD OF
SCANDAL.
IT SOUNDS LIKE SOMEONE THAT IS
DECIDING TO DO SOMETHING ELSE.
>> IF SHE HAS BEEN IN THE
ADMINISTRATION AND SHE HASN'T
HAD A SCANDAL WHY NOT STICK
AROUND?
>> BECAUSE LINDA McMAN, SHE IS A
COMPLETE.
SHE DID A LOT OF STUFF AROUND
THE COUNTRY.
SHE HAS GOT BIG PLANS AHEAD FOR
HER AND FOR DONALD TRUMP.
I THINK IT'S A GREAT MOVE FOR
HER.
I THINK IT MAKES A LOT OF SENSE
AND I THINK IT'S GREAT.
>> OKAY.
SO LEST TALK ABOUT BETSY DEVOSS.
THIS IS AFTER A DUST-UP WITH THE
PRESIDENT OVER SPECIAL OLYMPICS.
>> I'M GLAD YOU'RE EDUCATION
SECRETARY ARE YOU?
>> I AM INDEED.
MOST DAYS I AM.
>> MAYBE NOT THIS WEEK.
>> QUICK ON HER FEET THERE TO
INJECT A LITTLE HUMOR.
SHE HAD TO DEFEND THE CUT OF
SPECIAL OLYMPICS FUNDING IN THE
BUDGET AND THE PRESIDENT JUST
SAID HE WAS OVERRIDING HER.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE SHE KNEW SHE
WAS FED UP.
THE PRESIDENT DIDN'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW, THESE BUDGET
DOCUMENTS, THERE IS
STATEMSTATEMENT OF
VALUES.
ARE WE REALLY TRYING TO SAY THEY
DIDN'T HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT WAS
GOING TO BE IN THE BUDGET?
IT CAME AS A TOTAL SURPRISE?
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
IF IT DIDN'T IT SET HIM UP FOR
HIS FAVORITE THING WHICH IS TO
COME IN AND BE THE GOOD GUY AND
OT
OVERRIDE HIS PEOPLE.
>> SO WHEN HE SAYS THAT HE SAID
I DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT THIS UNTIL
THURSDAY YOU JUST DON'T --
>> REALLY?
>> YOU JUST DON'T TAKE HIM --
>> HE'S NOT SOMEONE KNOWN TO
TELL THE TRUTH VERY OFTEN.
I THINK IT'S --
>> HE DOESN'T LOOK GOOD
ADMITTING THAT EITHER THOUGH.
>> BUT JUST MASSIVE DOCUMENTS
ACROSS -- THAT SPAN THE ENTIRE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT I CAN SEE HIM
NOT KNOWING IT.
WAS IT BONE HEADED?
ABSOLUTELY.
IT IS TO YOUR POINT A STATEMENT
OF VALUES.
IT LOOKS PRETTY STUPID.
CONGRESS WOULD HAVE NEVER GONE
ALONG WITH IT.
AT THE END OF THE DAY IT IS
EMBARRASSMENT.
IT SO THE PICK THE NEW STATE
DEPARTMENT SPOKESPERSON.
IT IS A PRETTY PROMINENT ROLE.
IT ORTAGUS IS REPLACING.
YOU SERVED IN THIS EXACT ROLE.
I WONDER WHAT YOU TLI ABOUT THIS
PICK AND JUST THIS CONSTANT
POLLING FROM FOX NEWS FOR THESE
POSITIONS WITHIN THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION.
>> I DON'T KNOW HER.
I THINK IT SHOULD BE SEPARATED
FROM A CONCERNING ALIGNMENT I
THINK WE SHOULD GIVE HEAR SHOT.
MANY PEOPLE ARE CONCERNED BY THE
MEDIA HAPPENING BETWEEN FOX NEWS
AND THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> IF I COULD SAY I AM SOMEONE
THAT KNOWS HER.
TO SORT OF CLASSIFY HER AS A FOX
NEWS CONTRIBUTE TO I THINK
REALLY UNDERSELLS A LOT OF WHAT
SHE WILL BE ABLE TO BRING TO THE
ADMINISTRATION.
SHE IS COMING IN BEING SOMEONE
THAT IS ABLE TO BE A GOOD
SPOKESPERSON BUT BEING ABLE TO
PIVOT.
IT WON'T BE ABOUT HER OWN VIEWS
BUT ABOUT THE VIEWS OF THE
ADMINISTRATION.
IT INCLUDES TOP KEY
COMMUNICATIONS JOBS, OTHER
DEPARTMENTS.
ARE THERE ANY RISKS ASSOCIATED
WITH THIS?
>> NOT FOR THE PRESIDENT, NO.
>> IT IS HIS NETWORK.
HE IS NOT A HUGE FAN.
THAT'S OKAY.
FOR HIM HE LOVES FOX.
THERE IS ABSOLUTELY NO DOWNSIDE.
>> HE WATCHES A LOT OF CNN.
>> THAT IS ABSOLUTELY TRUE.
HE ABSOLUTELY DOES AS MADE CLEAR
BY HIS TWEETING.
AT THE END OF THE DAY THERE IS
NO DOWNSIDE.
IF YOU LOOK AT REPUBLICAN VOTERS
GET A LOT OF THEIR NEWS AT THE
END OF THE DAY THERE IS A LOT OF
GOOD SOLID AND GOOD PEOPLE.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S THAT MUCH
DOWNSIDE.
IT IS ABOUT WHAT SHE CAN DO.
>> I MEAN MORE BROADLY.
>> IF YOU LOOK AT HER JOBS SHE
HAD WORKED IN GOVERNMENTS
BEFORE.
SHE IS SOMEBODY THAT HAS BECOME
AND --
>> THIS ONE MAKES MORE SENSE.
>> IT DOES.
I THINK FOX ANCHORS ARE TALKING
FOR THE ADMINISTRATION.
THAT'S UNACCEPTABLE.
I DON'T THINK IT SHOULD REFLECT
ON HER AND HER ABILITY TO DO --
OR US ALLOWING US TO DO THIS
JOB.
>> SHOW ME THE■■
SOMEONE IS PREPARING FOR A BUZZ
KILL.
The day after chemo
might mean a trip back
to the doctor's office
just for a shot.
But why go back there
when you can stay home
with Neulasta Onpro?
Strong chemo can put you at
risk of serious infection.
In aey study Neulasta
reduced the risk of infection
from 17% to 1%,
a 94% decrease.
Neulasta Onpro is designed
to deliver Neulasta
the day after chemo
and is used by most pa today.
Neulasta is for certain
cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta if you're
allergic to it
eupogen (filgrastim).
An incomplete dose could
increase infection risk.
Ruptured spleen,
sometimes fatal as well as
serious lung problems,
allergic reactions,
kidney injuries and capillary
leak syndrome have occurred.
Report abdominal or shoulder
tip pain, trouble breathing
or allergic reactions to
your doctor right away.
In patients with sickle
celcan sorders,■■ somets
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
If you'd rather be home,
ask your doctor about
with copay card.÷■÷■÷  e
■/■■■
This is Huntsville, Alabama.
AKA, Rocket City, USA.
This is a very difficult job.
Failure is not an option.
More than half of employees
across the country
bring financial stress to work.
If you're stressed out
financially at home,
you're going to be too worried
to be able to do a good job.
I want to be able to offer all
of the benefits
that keep them satisfied.
It is the people that is really
the only asset that you have.
Put your employees on a path
to financial wellnessdent.
Bring your challenges.
There are people out there
who see things others can't.
They're the ones who see a city
that make those who live
in it feel a little safer.
Who see the efficient shape and
design of the ocean's wonders
as the future of aerodynamics.
■d■d Dell Technologies,
Who see the efficient shape and
design we see it too. wonders
If you'd like to transform
your business, talk to us.
And we'll show the world what
impossible looks like...
when it's made real.
♪♪
So, recently my son's band was
signed by a record label.
A record deal?
Unbelievable.
Whenever we're about to get
on a stage for a huge audience,
I always give my dad, like,
a FaceTime kinda moment.
You see the crowd,
you see the emotion.
You know, he has that experience
for the first time with me,
and that's really
important to me.
I created a rockstar.
(both laughing)
(announcer)
The best network is even better
when you share it.
Buy the latest iPhone for you,
and get iPhone 10R on us
for someone else.
And get Apple Music on us, too.
Only on Verizon.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
We're the Tenney's
and we're USAA members for life.
Call USAA to start saving
on insurance today.
>> DO YOU WANT THE WHITE HOUSE?
>> I HAVE CONFIDENCE.
IF THAT'S WHAT THEY WOULD LIKE
TO DO I HAVE NOTHING TO HIDE.
THIS WAS A HOAX AND A WITCH
HUNT.
I THINK THINGS ARE M COING OUT
WITH RESPECT TO THE OTHER SIDE.
>> ARE YOU TALK TO GO PRESIDENT
PUTIN?
>> HE SAID HE HAD NOTHING TO
HIDE.
WHAT DID YOU MAKE OF WHAT HE
SAID?
>> HE ALSO SAID THINK THERE
WILL BE THINGS COMING OUT ABOUT
THE OTHER SIDE.
NOW, THE ABSURDITY OF THAT
BECAUSE RUSSIA DID HELP DONALD
TRUMP GET ELECTED TO WHAT DEGREE
IT IS HARD TO KNOW.
?
WITH RESPECT TO YOU BOTH THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE DID BRING
UP VARIOUS TO ANSWER SOME
QUESTIONS.
THEY WILL BE UNVEILING REPORTS
THEMSELVES.
I THINK IF WE LOOK AT WHAT
HAPPENED IN THE 2016 ELECTION
THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT
HAVE 20 ANSWER FOR WHAT
HAPPENED.
THAT'S INCLUDING PEOPLE IN THE
OBAMA ADMINISTRATION AS WELL.
I THINK WE WANT TO HAVE A FULL
ACCOUNT OF WHAT HAPPENED.
IT MAKES PERFECT SENSE.
>> I HAVE TO SAY WHAT YOU JUST
SAID IS PRETTY OFFENSIVE.
>> WHY?
>> THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION WAS
IN.
HE GATHERED AND ASKED THEM TO
DIG DEEP AND GET EVERYTHING IN
PUBLIC SO THAT THE FUTURE
ADMINISTRATION AND ALL OF THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY COULD
HELP PRESIDENT TRUMP.
WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP AND HIS
TEAM DID IS HAVE ALL SORTS OF
SKETCHY MEETINGS.
WE KNOW ABOUT HIS BUSINESS TIES.
THERE ARE LOTS OF QUESTIONS.
>> WE HEARD IT WAS McCONNELL.
HE SAID --
>> HOLD ON.
>> PRESIDENT OBAMA SAID HE WENT
TO THE BIPARTISAN LEADERSHIP OF
THE CONGRESS AND SAID WE SHOULD
PUT THIS ALL OUT IN THE PUBLIC.
WHO DIDN'T WANT TO DO IT?
>> YEAH.
>> HE DOES NOT RUN THE CIA.
HE DOES NOT RUN THE DEFENSE
DEPARTMENT, THE STATE
DEPARTMENT, ANY OF THE EXECUTIVE
BRANCH.
HE RUNS ONE-HALF OF ONE-THIRD OF
THE GOVERNMENT.
WHAT WAS ASKED BACK IN SEPTEMBER
WAS IF BY THE
OBAMAADMINISTRATION.
IT IS TO SAY BE VIGILANT IN
MAKING SURE ELECTIONS SYSTEMS
WERE SECURE.
>> AND WE HAVE TO LEAVE THIS
PART OF OUR CONVERSATION THERE.
IN OUR 2020 LEAD MONEY IS
TALKING.
DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES FACING ONE
IN THE PRESIDENTIAL RACE.
THIS IS THE FIRST FUNDRAISING
DEADLINE OF THE 2020 CYC
>> WE WILL■ TOGETHER■
STRONGEST GRASS ROOTS MOVEMENT
IN THE HISTORY OF AMERICAND<
POLITICS.
>> RAISING MONEY ON THE
DAY OF THE CAMPAIGN THEY ARE
SCRAMBLING TO MEELT THE FIRST
FUNDRAISING DETD LINE ON SUDNDA.
>> RAISING MONEY SO THIS IS A
TOPIC THAT WE DON'T LIKE TO
DISCUSS, BUT YOU CAN'T WIN AN
ELECTION WITHOUT KNOWING HOW TO
RAISE Y.
>> SUDDENLY HARRIS IS TRYING TO
LOWER EXPECTATIONS TELLING
DONORS WE KNOW SOME OF THEM WILL
HAVE OUTRAISED US.
I CAN GUARANTEE WE WON'T BE AT
WORK.
AS FUNDRAISING APPEALS POUR IN
IT'S NOT HOW MUCH THEY RAISE BUT
HOW THEY RAISE IT.
>> AND TODAY THIS VERY DAY I'M
NOT OFF DOING A FUNDRAISER
BEHIND CLOSED DOORS WITH A BUNCH
OF MILLIONAIRES.
I'M HTH■ ■ SWEARING OFF HIGH DO
FUNDRAISING EVENTS TRYING TO
MATCH THE THEY HAVE SEEING IN
THE OPENING ROUND OF THE RACE.
>> A LOT OF FUNDRAISING THAT
GOES ON.
IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT■ GETTING TH
MOST DOLLARS.
THE MORE YOU HELP THE BETTER.
>> THE RECENT HAS TO CAPTURE
ENTHUSIASM INCLUDING A HIGH-RISE
APARTMENT AT THE TRUMP
INTERNATIONAL■■■■■■■77 NEW YORK.
THE■??■■óó■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■oo■
CANDIDATES ARE CATCHING ON AMONG
THOSE INSPIRES TO SEND IN SMALL
CONTRIBUTIONSMENT THEY ARE
LIMITING THE KIND OF MONEY THEY
ACCEPT.
>> I WILL NOT TAKE MONEY FROM
CORPORATE TAX.
THEY MUST HAVE AT LEAST 65,000
TO REACH THE DEBATE STAGE.
THE QUALIFYING FOR THAT DEBATE
STAGE IS FOR CON DAY DATS.
IT COULD CERTAINLY CLANG THE
ORDER BEFORE THAT.
AFTER TALKING TO SEVERAL DONORS
THIS WEEK A LOT OF THEM ARE
SITTING ON THE SIDELINES
WATCHING THIS PLAY OUT.
ONE SAID I'LL PROBABLY GIVE
MONEY TO A BUNCH OF THEM.
>> A BUNCH OF THEM.
>> ENOUGH TO GO AROUND.
THANK YOU MUCH.
>>> WHAT DO YOU THINK OF SENATOR
HARRIS?
SHE RAISED A MILLION AND A HALF
DOLLARS.
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE RAISED VERY
MUCH.
YOU LOOK AT BERNIE SANDERS.
SHE IS MANAGING EXPECTATIONS,
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT?
>> I THINK IT IS SMART.
AT THIS POINT MOST AMERICANS
AREN'T REALLY PAYING ATTENTION.
WE KNOW YOU HAD A GOOD LIST.
THAT
THESE ARE ALL OF THE LITTLE
INDICATORS I WAS LOOKING FOR.
I WOULD REMIND IT WAS JOHN
McCAIN.
>> AND JOHN EDWARDS THAT RAISED
IN THE FIRST QUARTER AND BLEW
EVERYONES MINDS.
I THINK I HAVE HEARD THE SAME
THING AS JEFF'S REPORTING.
A LOT OF HIGH DOLLAR DONORS ARE
HOLDING FUNDRAISERS FOR
DIFFERENT CANDIDATES.
LOW DOLLAR DONORS ARE DOING THE
SAME THING.
A LOT OF DEMOCRATS ARE SITTING
AND WAITING.
YOU HEAR THEM TALKING ABOUT WHO
IS THE MOST LIKELY CANDIDATE TO
BEAT DONALD TRUMP RIGHT?
>> LOOK, AT THE SAME TIME MAYOR
PETE BECAUSE I CAN'T PRONOUNCE
HIS LAST NAME, HE HAS BEEN
SHOOTING UP IN THE POLLS.
IT HELPED HIM RAISE MONEY AND
THAT'S HOW THE PROCESS SHOULD
WORK.
MORE PEOPLE ARE GETTING TO KNOW
HIM.
>> AND LET'S LISTEN TO MAY THE
MAYOR.
SO HE GOES UP TO CALIFORNIA TO
MEET VOTERS.
HE COMES DOWN ON WHAT COASTAL
LEADISM AND HE SAID HE FEELS
LIKE FROM THE MIDDLE OF THE
COUNTRY.
LET'S PLAN.
LISTEN.
>> I SEE A LOTLE KIND OFING THE
HOW, YOU KNOW, PEOPLE ESPECIALLY
WORKING CLASS PEOPLE THAT WORK
FOR CONSERVE TIFRS, HOW CAN YOU
VOTE AGAINST YOUR SELF-INTEREST?
DON'T YOU KNOW YOU'RE VOTING
AGAINST YOUR INTEREST?
IF YOU SAY THAT THEY COULD VERY
SIMPLY TURN AROUND AND SAY SO
ARE YOU.
THINGS LIKE HE'S THE SORT OF THE
PERSON I THINK REPUBLICANS OUGHT
TO BE QUITE NERVOUS ABOUT.
TO THE FUNDRAISING POINT HE WAS
ABLE TO RAISE A LOT OFF OF THESE
SORT OF VIRAL MOMENTS.
RATHER THAN THINKING WE ALWAYS
THINK HOW MUCH DID YOU RAISE
LAST QUARTER I THINK WHAT WILL
BE IMPORTANT OVER THE COURSE OF
THE NEXT YEAR, YEAR AND A HALF
WATCH HOW MUCH THEY RAISE OFF OF
THESE MOMENTS IN THE DEBATES
WHEN THEY GIVE SPEECHES AND
SOMETHING HAPPENS AND IT GOES
VIRAL AND THEY RAISE THE MONEY.
I THINK IT WILL BE THE FUZZ
RAISING FOR SURE.
>> DO YOU THINK REPUBLICANS
SHOULD WORRY ABOUT MAYOR PETE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> TELL US. DON'T■NOW.
>> HE IS NOT WORRIED.
>>NO.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE I KNOW ENOUGH
ABOUT THE.
I FEEL LIKE I READ STORIES.
THINGS CAN BE FOUND OUT.
I DON'T KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE I LOOK AND I'M NOT A
DEMOCRAT BUT THEY SORLTOVER
EXPLAINED HE NOT SURE WHAT LANE
SHE IN AND HOW HE CAN DO.
>> WE'LL CHECK IN WITH YOU IN
SIX MONTHS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SO THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
SHARING NUCLEAR SECRETS WITH
ANOTHER COMPANY AND KEEPING IT
FROM AMERICANS.
FIND OUT WHY NEXT.
Hello to quae
at Marco's.
Hello to the best part
of the day....
with Itality pizza.
Get two medium,
one-g pizzas for
just $6.99 each.■■■■■■
The Italian way.
Hello Primo.
Fact is, every insurance company
hopes you drive safely.■/■/■
But AllstaW÷s you
drive sa■■■■se.
you kn■oo
fast...
...and brake too hard.
With feedback to help you drive
safer.
Giving you the power to actually
lower your cost.
Now that you know the truth...
are you in Good Hands?
With Expedia,
I saved when I added
a hotel to our flight.
So even when
she grows up,
Unlock savings
when you add
select hotels to your
existing trip.
Only with Expedia.
select hotels to your
existing trip.
♪ oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ It's taking over ♪
♪ There's no escape ♪
♪ You better get moving ♪
♪ Ready or not ♪
♪ It's about to go down
here it comes now ♪
♪ Get ready ♪
♪ oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Moving ♪
♪ Ready or not ♪
♪ Get ready ♪
♪ oh oh oh oh oh ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪♪
[laughter]
"I'm ♪♪ay."@z@z@z
♪♪
>>> APPROVAL FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE?
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION ISSUED
ALLOWING U.S. ENERGY COMPANIES
TO SHARE&>■■8■ TECHNAL
DETAILS WITHOUT ANY GUARANTEE
THAT INFORMATION WON'T BE USED
TO DEVELOP A NUCLEAR WEAPONS
PROGRAM.
ALEX REPORTS.
IT IS O STRAINED
AND PIF TOLL MOMENTS.
SAUDI ARABIA TO RECEIVE AMERICAN
UNCLASSIFIED CIVIL NUCLEAR
TECHNOLOGY JUST FIVE MONTHS
AFTER SAUDI JOURNALIST WAS
KILLED.
U.S. INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES
BELIEVE THE ORDER CAME FROM
CROWN PRINCE.
IF THEY GO TO RUSSIA AND CHINA
FOR THEIR NUCLEAR PARTNERS I CAN
ASSURE YOU THAT THOSE TWO
COUNTRIES DON'T GIVE Axxxxxxx T.
>> IT CONTAINED ENERGY.
SAUDI ARABIA HAS NO NUCLEAR
WEAPONS FOR NOW.
THEY SAY IT COULD CHANGE IF IRAN
BUILDS THEM.
BY LAW THEY MUST AGREE TO
CONTROL TO PREVENT THEM FROM
DEVE NUCLEAR■O■#c#q
SO FAR SAUDI ARABIA HAS NOT
AGREED TO THOSE CONDITIONS.
>> IT APPEARS THIS IS AN END RU.
ZB SECRETARY OF STATE POMPEO
GRILLED ABOUT THE AUTHORIZATIONS
ON CAPITOL HILL.
>> WE TREATED IRAN LIKE AN
ENEMY.
IF SAUDI ARABIA AND HELD BENT ON
DEVELOPING A PROGRAM THAT IS
UNCONTROLLED AND DESIGNED TO
MAKE THEM A NUCLEAR STATE OR A
POSSIBLE NUCLEAR STATE WILL WE
TREAT THEM AS AN ENEMY.
>> WE ARE WORKING TO ENSURE IT
IS SOMETHING WE UNDERSTAND AND
DOESN'T PRESENT THAT■#■ RISK.
>> WHITE HOUSE SENIOR ADVISER
TOOK A QUIET TRIP TO THE
KINGDOM.
THE BROTHER OF THE CROWN PRINCE
WHO WAS THE AMBASSADOR TO THE
U.S. WHEN THEY TRIED TO COIN
VINCE HIM HIS FRIEND TOLD CNN IT
WOULD BE SAFE TO RETURN TO SAUDI
ARABIA.
RICK PERRY WAS ASKED
SPECIFICALLY WHETHER THE
AUTHORIZATIONS TO SELL THAT WERE
APPROVED AFTER OCTOBER 2nd.
THAT'S THE DAY HE WAS KILLED BY
A SAUDI HIT TEAM IN ISTANBUL.
PERRY RESPONDED SAYING HE DIDN'T
KNOW SAYING WE SIGN A LOT OF
PAPERS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
>>> LET'S DISCUSS WITH FORMER
CIA AND FBI OFFICIAL PHIL MUD.
YOU DID SERVE AS A CONSULTANT TO
THE SAUDI INTERIOR MINISTRY FROM
2010 TO 2011.
WHAT DOES THIS SAY THAT NUCLEAR
SECRETS ARE BEING SHARED, THAT
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE HAVEN'T
KNOWN ABOUT THEM?
WHAT DOES IT SAY ABOUT U.S.
FOREIGN POLICY?
>> I GUESS THERE'S A COUPLE OF
QUESTIONS YOU WOULD ASK.
WE WANT TO MAKE MONEY.
WE WANT TO SELL STUFF INCLUDING
THE SAUDIS AND WE WANT TO
CONFRONT THE IRANIANS.
IT IS IN THE ARABIA PENINSULA.
IT IS IN THE SAID DI GUDI GOVER.
THE MURDER ED A CITIZEN FIVE
MONTHS AGO.
HE WROTE THE UNITED STATES
NEWSPAPERS.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO GIVE A
BENEFIT TO THE KINGDOM WHAT ARE
YOU ASKING OF ME IN RETURN?
WE GAVE HIM SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WE GOT.
>> IS THIS A SIGN WITH THE
INTEREST OF TRYING TO HAVE AT
LEAST AN ALLY UP AGAINST IRAN
THERE POTENTIALLY BEING A
NUCLEAR POWER IS THIS A SIGN
THAT THE U.S. IS FOREGOING
LEVERAGE ESPECIALLY AS YOU LOOK
AT HOW THEY HAVE BEEN TREATED BY
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION?
>> I THINK IT IS.
I'M NOT SURE WHY WE GAVE UP THAT
LEVERAGE.
TO TALK ABOUT WHAT YOU GET FOR
PROVIDING NUCLEAR TECHNOLOGY IT
DOESN'T SEEM TO ME OUT OF THE
QUESTION TO SAY LOOK, WE WANT TO
REMAIN PARTNERS.
WE DON'T LIKE THE IRANIANS.
WE WANT TO GIVE YOU NUCLEAR
TECHNOLOGY.
YOU JUST MURDERED A CITIZEN.
WE WILL APPLY SANCTIONS AGAINST
YOU.
I DON'T SEE WHY WE DON'T HAVE
OUR CAKE AND EAT IT TOO.
I DON'T THINK IT'S A BAD IDEA.
MY QUESTION IS WHY DON'T WE MAKE
THEM HURT IN EXCHANGE OF THEIR
MURDERED SOMEBODY WHO WAS AN
AUTHOR?
BHU DO WE HAVE OUR CAKE AND EAT
IT TOO?
I DON'T GET IT.
>> THANK YOU FOR YOUR INCITE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP THREATENING TO
SHUT DOWN THE U.S./MEXICO
BORDER.
WE HAVE A LOOK AT WHAT'S REALLY
HAPPENING  ED.
>> Reporter: PEOPLE ARE ASKING
IS THIS REAL OR MAN FUFACTURED?
I'LL HAVE THAT STORY COMING UP.
■
n
♪ ♪
♪ Just hold on, I'm comin' ♪
♪ Hold on, I'm comin' ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ Don't you worry, I'm comin' ♪
♪ Here I come ♪
I thought I married an Italian.
My lineage was the Vecchios and
Zuccolis. Through Ancestry,
through DNA I found out that I
was only 16% Italian.
He was 34% Eastern European.
So I went onto Ancestry,
soon learned that one of our
ancestors we thought was Italian
was Eastern European.
This is my ancestor who I
didn't know about.
He looks a little bit
like me, yes.
Ancestry has many paths to
discovering your story.
Get started for free at
Ancestry.com
>>> I WILL CLOSE THE BORDER IF
MEXICO Dá> WITH IT.
>> CALLING THE BORDER A
CASCADINGú CRISI ASKING IF I
WAS TO FULLY SHUT THE BORDER.
A SENIOR OFFICIAL SAID NOT AS OF
NOW.
TELL US WHAT YOU'RE SEEING
THERE.
>> WELL, OVER THE COURSE OF THE
LAST WEEK WE HAVE SEEN SENIOR
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION OFFICIALS
SOUND THE ALARM ABOUT WHAT'S
HAPPENING HERE ON THE SOUTHERN
BORDER.
CRITICS SAY THEY DON'T SEE THAT
URGENCY.
EVERY DAY THIS WEEK THEY HAVE
DROPPED OFF ON THE DOORSTEP IN
BROWNSVILLE, TEXAS.
MOST ARE WREQUESTING ASYLUM.
HE JOHNS OF VOLUNTEERS SCRAMBLE
TO HELP MOTHERS AND FATHERS WITH
THEIR CHILDREN.
>> WE SEE THAT IT BEING A TOOL
IN A LARGER POLITICAL GAIN GAME
THAT IS COMPLETELY TO WHAT THE
COMMUNITIES HERE WANT.
>> GOOD NEIGHBOR SETTLEMENT IS
ONE OF SEVERAL SHELTERS HELPING
SUDDENLY RELEASE THIS WEEK BY
CUSTOMS AND BORDER PROTECTION.
THE AGENCY SAYS IT CAN'T HANDLE
THE MASIVE NUMBER.
>> IT WAS AT THE BREAKING POINT.
IT HAS ARRIVED THIS WEEK AT OUR
BORDER.
>> THEY ARE ON PACE FOR ON REHE
THINKS AND ENCOUNTERS FOR MORE
THAN 100,000 MIGRANTS IN MARA■■
IS IN■x FREE FALL.■%■#■#
PRESTRUMP SAYS THE
TENSOVER THOUS MIGRANTS
ARE CARRYINGnnn A BIG FAT AND
TLTENNING TO CONTROL ILLEGAL
IMMIGRATION.
>> AND WE ARE ON TRACK FOR A
MILLION ILLEGAL ALIENS TRYING TO
RUSH OUR BORDER.
IT IS AN INVASION.
>> WE MET HER AND HER DAUGHTER
AT THE DAUGHTER IN BROWNSVILLE.
THEY ASKED WE NOT SHOW THEIR
FACES BECAUSE THEY FEAR BEING
RETURNED.
SHE SAYS SHE FLED HER HOME
COUNTRY BECAUSE THEY FEARE
BEING KILLED.
GANG MEMBERS MURDERED HER MOTHER
LAST YEAR.
■x■x■x■x■x■x■x■x
HER DAUGHTER SAYS THREE POLICE
OFFICERS UNLEASHED A BRAUZING
ATTACK.
KICKING AND PUNCHING HER FOR
REASONS THAT WERE NEVER CLEAR.
THAT'S WHEN THEY DECIDED TO
LEAVE.
ADVOCATES SAY IT IS NOT A CON
JOB BUT REAL TEEMw■Twíwíwí LIFE■
ANH KWENS KWONS
>> WE KNO■ T'SNING.
>> THEY SAY THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION IS TRYING TO --
AND GIVING FAMILIES CONFUSING
PAPERWORK.
>> THIS IS ONE OF THE MIGRANTS
HERE THAT ASKED US NOT TO
IDENTIFY HER.
THESE ARE THE FORMS THEY ARE
GIVEN.
IF YOU LOOK CLOSELY IT IS
SUPPOSED TO BE A NOTICE GIVING
THEM A DATE AND TIME WHEN THEY
SUPPOSED TO APPEAR.
HERE THEY ARE NOT GETTING TOEZ
DATES.
>> THEY SAY THERE IS NO
MANUFACTURED CRISIS AND THERE IS
A REAL HUMANITARIAN AND SECURITY
CRISIS UNFOLDING.
THEY WERE MASS RELEASES INTENDED
TO THE ALREADY FRAGILE
INFRASTRUCTURE.
>> SO YOU THINK IT'S DELIBERATE?
>> YES.
>> AND THIS THREAT BY PRESIDENT
TRUMP TO SHUT DOWN AND CLOSE
PORTS OF ENTRY SENT SHOCK WAVES
ACROSS THE BORDER.
YOU CAN SEE THERE WERE MILLIONS
OF PEOPLE THAT USE THOSE KIND OF
BRIDGES AND PATHS TO CROSS BACK
AND FORTH EVERY DAY.
THEY DEPEND ON IT.
>> VERY GOOD POINT THANK YOU.
JOIN US 9:00 A.M. ON SUNDAY.
THAT'S IT FOR THE LEAD TODAY.
FOLLOW ME ON