RATHER THAN HAVING IT DOWN
LOADED AUTOMATICALLY.
>> AND YOU JUST MAKE THE
ANNOUNCEMENT AS YOU POINTED OUT
THAT'S VERY IMPORTANT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, SIR.
YOU CAN FOLLOW ME ON FACEBOOK
AND TWITTER OR TWEET THE SHOW AT
THE LEAD CNN AND OUR COVERAGE ON
CNN CONTINUES RIGHT■  NOW.
>> CHARGED WITH LYING TO POLICE.
I'LL TALK TO CALLING IT A WHITE
WASH.
GREAT REPORT AFTER MONTHS OF
TOSSING AROUND PHRASES LIKE
WITCH HUNT AND HOAX PRESIDENT
TRUMP CALLS ROBERT MUELLER'S
REPORT GREAT.
HE FALSELY CLAIMS IT EXONE
GIULIANI IS HERE IN THE
SITUATION ROOM LIVE.
WE PEEL AND REPEAL AS THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION TO A ELIMINATE
THE ACT.
WHY DEMOCRATS FEEM THEY HAVE A
NEW WEAPON.
IS IT A MESSAGE TO NORTH KOREA?
I'M WOLF OF BLITZER.
YOU'RE IN THE■■■ SITUATION ROOM.
>>> THEY FURIOUS WHO CALLS IT A
WHITE WASH OF JUSTICE.
ALSO AS THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
SAYS IT WILL TAKE WEEKS TO
RELEASE THE MUELLER REPORT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SEIZES TO
DECLARE VICTORY WHILE FALSELY
CLAIMING THAT THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL EXONERATED HIM OF
OBSTRUCTION.
THE PRESIDENT IS USING MUELLER'S
FINDINGS TO ATTACK CRITICS.
IT MAY HAVE JUST GIVEN DEMOCRATS
A 2020 BATTLE CRY WITH A NEW
EFFORT TO GET RID OF OBAMACARE.
RUDY GIULIANI IS STANDING BY.
LET'S BEGIN WITH TODAY'S
SHOCKING DEVELOPMENTS IN THE
SMOLLETT CASE.
SO HOW IS EVERYONE EXPLAINING
THIS EXTRAORDINARY TURN OF
EVENTS.
>> RIGHT NOW THEY ARE NOT.
IT HAS BEEN AHEAD SKRAFRPING
FROM THE PUBLIC TO THE MAYOR'S
OFFICER.
PEOPLE WANT TO KNOW HOW HE ENDED
UP HERE.
THE JUDGE HAS SEALED THIS CASE.
HT CHICAGO OFFICIALS FUR■
USE.
FURIOUS.
>> WHERE DO I THINK JUSTICE IS
THIS?
I THINK THIS CITY IS STILL
AN APOLOGY.
>> ALL CHARGES WERE DROPPED
AFTER HE WAS ACCUSED OF STAGING
AN ATTACK TO LOOK LIKE A HATE
CRIME.
>> WE FOUND OUT ABOUT WHEN YOU
ALL DID.
>> OFFICIALS CLAIMING THAT IT
WAS A HOAX.
THE STATE SEALING ALL OF THE
EVIDENCE IN THE CASE.
>> CLOSE TO HIDE BEHIND SECRECY
AND BROKER A DEAL.
MY DEAL IS TOTIGATE AN
INCIDENT, GATHER EVIDENCE AND
GATHER FACTS AND PRESENT THEM TO
THAT'S WHAT WE DID.
I STAND BEHIND THE
INVESTIGATION.
>> TODAY SMOLLETT TOOK A VICTORY
LAP AT THE COURTHOUSE.
>> I HAVE BEEN TRUTHFUL ON EVERY
LEVEL SINCE DAY ONE.
I WOULD NOT BE MY MOTHER'S SON
I WAS CAPABLE OF ONE DROP
THAT I'M ACCUSED OF.
>> KEEPING IN MIND RESOURCES IS
TO COMBAT VIOLENT CRIME AND THE
DRIVERS OF VIOLENCE.
THE DECISIONED TO■÷ OFFER
THIS DISPOSITION IN THE CASE.
>> HIS LAWYERS EARLIER POINTING
FINGERS AT CHICAGO POLICE.
>> WE HAVE NOTHING TO SAY TO THE
POLICE DEPARTMENT EXCEPT TO
INVESTIGATE CHARGE AND NOT TRY
THEIR CASES IN THE PRESS TO
BRING CHARGES AND TO0] JUMP
AHEAD AND UTILIZE THE PRESS TO
CONVICT PEOPLE BEFORE THEY ARE
TRIED IN A COURT OF LAW.
>> QUITE FRANKLIN IT EVERYBODY
OFF.
>> STRONG WORDS BY
SUPERINTENDENT ANNOUNCING
CHARGES AGAINST SMOLLETT.
>> AND WHY THIS STUNT WAS ORK
STRAITED BECAUSE HE WAS DITS
DISSATISFIED ABOUT HIS SALARY.
>> CHICAGO'S MAYOR.
>> NOT ONLY IS IT $10,000 BUT
ALL OF THE OTHER REPERCUSSIONS
IT MADE TO ME, WHERE IS THE
ACCOUNTABILITY OF THE SYSTEM?
YOU CANNOT HAVE BECAUSE OF A
PERSON'S POSITION ONE SET OF
RULES APPLY TO THEM AND ANOTHER
SET OF RULES APPLY TO EVERYBODY
ELSE.
>> WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT THIS IT
GOT INTERNATIONAL ATTENTION.
I'M TOLD THOSE TWO MEN HAVE THE
TEXT MESSAGE EXCHANGES BETWEEN
SMOLLETT AND THEMSELVES SO THEY
A LOT OF QUESTIONS WITH THIS.
NOW THAT IT'S SEALED WE PLAY
NEVER KNOW WHAT POLICE ACTUALLY
HAD.
>> THIS IS RYAN YOUNG FOR US.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON THIS BREAKING
NEWS COMING UP LATER IN THE
SITUATION ROOM.
I'LL SPEAK LATER WITH HIM.
OTHER BIG STORIES INCLUDING
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HE IS NOW GOING ON THE OFFENSIVE
IN THE WAKE OF A MUELLER REPORT
AT LEAST THE SUMMARY THAT IS
RELEASED.
HI■■ID■■■■■O■O W■■■■        ■■■k
■■■SEL FOUND HE DID N ENGAGE O■■
IN ■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
■■P■■■■■■■■■■■PT
A CLEAR HEALTH CARE PLAN OF ITS
OWN.
SOAK IN THE FINDINGSO OF
ROBERT MUELLER'S REPORT HE
DIDN'T STICK TO THE FACTS.
>> THE MUELLER REPORT WAS GREAT.
IT COULD NOT HAVE BEEN BETTER.
IT SAID NO OBSTRUCTION, NO
COLLUSION.
IT COULD NOT HAVE BEEN BETTER.
>> BUT THAT'S NOT TRUE.
WHILE ATTORNEY GENERAL SUMMARY
DID STATE THAT THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL FOUND THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN
DID NOT CONSPIRE THE QUESTION OF
OBSTRUCTION WAS LEFT TO THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT AND IT WAS
BAR AND DEPUTY ATTORNEYERAL
WHO DECIDED NOT TO PROSECUTE.■#
PRESIDENT'S WORD FOR IT AND
DEMANDING TO SEE THE FULL
REPORT.
THEY DON'T NEED AN
INTERPRETATION BY AN ATTORNEY
GENERAL APOINTED FOR A
PARTICULAR JOB TO MAKE SURE THE
PRESIDENT IS WE NEED TO SEE THE
REPORT.
>> PRESIDENT ALSO ACCUSED
UNSPECIFIED FORCES OF
CONSPIREING AGAINST HIM.
>> WE CANNOT LET IT EVER HAPPEN
AGAIN.
IT WENT VERY HIGH UP AND IT
STARTED FAIRLY LOW BUT WITH
INSTRUCTIONS FROM THE HIGHP
THIS SHOULD NEVER HAPPEN TO A
PRESIDENT AGAIN.
WE ISN'T ALLOW THAT TO TAKE
PLACE.
>> MR. TRUMP ACCUSED THE OBAMA
WARE WHITE HOUSE OF SWIER
TAPPING HIM.
ONE OF THE PRESIDENT'S TOP ALLY
SAYS HE URGED TO GIVE THE
DOSSIER TO THE FBI.
>> HE CALLED ME UP AND SAID WHAT
DO YOU THINK?
SHOULD I TURN IT OVER TO THE
FBI?
I SAID YES.
>> ONE AREA THERE IS AGREEMENT
IMPEACHMENT AGREES TO BE OFF THE
TABLE.
>> IT IS NOT OFF OF THE TABLE
UNTIL IN THE TABLE.
>>.
>> THE FEDERAL JUNL'S RULING
SAYING IN A STIMT THE COMP HEN
IFR AGREEMENT.
HE JUMPED IN AND DID DAMAGE
CONTROL.
>> THE REPUBLICAN PARTY WILL
SOON BE KNOWN ADDS THE PARTY OF
HEALTH CARE.
YOU WATCH.
>> HE VOWED TO TAKE CARE OF
PEOPLE WITH PREEXISTING
CONDITIONS.
PROTECTIONS. OBAMACARE'S KEY
>> I WILL ALWAYS FIGHT FOR AND
ALWAYS PROTECT PATIENTS WITH
>> AFTERy■[X■■■■ú PROTECTING
OBAMACARE IN THE MIDTERMS
DETERD
DEMOCRATS ARE MORE THAN READY.
>> IT T A■■■■■■ TWO-YEAR ANCHOR
■■■■ THE NA■A■AsAsA■■s■sA■■■EAS.
CONFIRMED TO IS ATTORNEY IS
@;@;@;@; PARDON THE ■■■s■sIDENT.
HE TOLD CNN IQ■■■@■■Q■■■■■■■■■■
WOULD ■■■■■■Q■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■.
THIDENT HAQ■Q■Q■■■■■         SU.
HE HAS TOLD REPORTERS HE HASN'T
GIVEN IT A LOT OF THOUGHT YET.
>> THANKS VERY MUCH.
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S PERSONAL TONE
GIULIANI, THE FORMER MAYOR OF
THANKS FOR COMING IN.
>> NICE TO BE HERE.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL'S SUMMARY.
DO YOU HAVE A COPY OVER THERE?
>> I'M READY.
>> THE PRESIDENT IS NOW SAYING
THAT THE MUELLER REPORT IN HIS
WORD IS GREAT AND THAT ROBERT
MUELLER WHO SPENT NEARLWO
YEARS INVESTIGATING ALL OF THIS
ACTED HONORABLY.
DO YOU AGREE WITH THE PRESIDENT?
>> N THAT HE ACTED ON HONORABLY.
>> TELL US WHY YOU WOULD HAVE TO
DISAGREE.
>> WE HAVE HAD -- YOU KNOW,
PEOPLE SEE IT DIFFERENTLY.
MAYBE I WAS IN THE TRENCHES
MORE.
I THOUGHT THAT TREATMENT OF
MANAFORT WAS WAY OVER THE TOP.
IT THINK IT SHOULDN'T BE
ALLOWED.
THEY SHOULD TAKE THEM, PUT THEM
IN SOLITARYONFINEMENT
BASICALLY TELLING THEM WHAT YOU
>/LY. THEY LYINGUT.>]O SAYING H■
■=■=■=■■■■■■■■
PARDONS.
I HAVE TAKEN THE SAME POSITION
FROM DAY ONE UNTIL NOW.
>> HE WAS TREATED THERE ALMOST A
GROSSLY HORRIBLE WAY.
>> AND YOU PLEADED GUILTY.
>> YEAH BUT HE NEVER SAID WHAT
THEY WANTED HIM TO SAY.
HE GOT THAT BIG LONG SENTENCE.
>> HE IS ABOUT TO GO TO JAIL FOR
SEVEN AND A HALF YEAR.
>> I'M NOT SAYING HE IS
BLAMELESS.
I'M TELLING YOU, HE WAS TREATED
HORRIBLY.
HE WAS TREATED I A WAY THAT'S
VERY VERY DANGEROUS.
A PROSECUTOR COMES VERY CLOSELY
TO THAT.
YOU PUT A CERTAIN AMOUNT OF
PRESSURE ON SOMEBODY.
THAT'S POINT AT WHICH YOU KNOW
I'M PUTTING TOO MUCH PRESSURE
ON.
MAY GHAT I WANT TO HEAR
BUT IT MAY NOT BE TRUE.
>> IF SOMEBODY WAS STEALING
MILLIONS AND MILLIONS OF DOLLARS
NOT FILING TAX RETURNS THE WAY
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO FILE,
WOULDN'T YOU GO AFTER THAT
INDIVIDUAL?
>> OF COURSE WE WOULD.
>> OF COURSE I WOULD.
I WOULDN'T RAID HIS HOUSE.
I WOULD NOT PUT HIM IN SOLITARY
CONFINEMENT.
THAT'S CRAZY.
MOST TERRORISTS AREN'T IN
SOLITARY CONFINEMENT.
>> LET ME ASK YOU THIS --
>> MAY I FINISH THE SENTENCE YOU
TO LET ME FINISH THE SENTENCE.
>> POWELL WROTE A BOOK CALLED --
I HAVE FORGOT THE NAME OF THE
BOOK BUT IT'S A BOOK ABOUT ABUSE
OF POWER.
>> HE WAS ONE OF THE PROSECUTORS
WORKING.
>> HE WAS HANDLING THE MANAFORT
CASE.
13 TIMES BACK AND FORTH THE GUY
WAS IN SOLITARY.
THEY CONTENDED THAT HE KNEW THAT
THE PRESIDENT DID NOT HAVE
MEETING WITH THAT RUSSIAN WOMAN.
>> AND HE CONTENDED HE DID NOT?
>> YES.
EACH TIME THEY WOULD SAY YOU'RE
LIE, YOU'RE LYING, YOU'RE LYING.
WE HAPPEN TO HAVE THAT MATERIAL
SENT TO US.
IT WAS KIND OF A BIG DEAL AT THE
TIME THAT IT■= HAPPENED.
>> IN HIS LETTER I HAVE A COPY
THAT HE DID INTERFERE IN THE
U.S. PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION IN
2016.
>> YOU NEVER DISCUSSED THAT?
>> THE PRESIDENT DOESN'T
DISAGREE RUSSIANS INTERFERED.
WHAT HE DISAGREED WITH IS THAT
HE HAD ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT.
>> LISTEN TO WHAT THE PRESIDENT
SAID AFTER HE MET WITH, YOU
KNOW, WITH THE RUSSIAN LOOET
LEADER.
>> IT IS KIND OF SWITCHING.
>> THE HEADLINE HERE IS --
>> HOLD ON A SECOND.
>> AFTER TWO YEARS OF SAYING
COLLUSION, COLLUSION, COLLUSION
ON THIS NETWORK THE WHOLE
PURPOSE OF MUELLER'S.
>> OF COURSE HE■> WAS.
SIT THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT'S
EFFORTS TO INTERFERE IN THE 2016
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION.
THEY INVESTIGATED THAT.
THEY CONFIRMED THAT.
IT'S IN THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
SUMMARY OF THE MUELLER REPORT.
IT INTRIGUED ME WHY THE
PRESIDENT MAYBE REFUSES TO STILL
ACCEPT THAT.
LISTEN TO WHAT HE SAID.
LISTEN TO THIS.
I HAVE PRESIDENT PUTIN.
HE SAID IT'S NOT RUSSIA.
I WILL SAY THIS, I DON SEE ANY
REASON WHY IOULD BE.
>> I MEAN THAT'S CLE THE
WHOLE OBJECTIVE WHILE THE
RUSSIANS INTERFERED IN THE
PRESIDENT SHLG ELECTION.
THE U.S. INTELLIGENCE CONCLUDED
THEY HAD THREE GOALS.
TO HARM ELECT BLT, HELP DONALD
TRUMP'S ELECTION CHANCE AND
UNDER DPTS MINE.
WHY WON'T THE PRESIDENT ACCEPT
WHAT HIS OWN INTELLIGENCE TELLS
HIM?
>> HE SAYS THIS IS A VERY GOOD
REPORT AND I AGREE IT IS A VERY
VERY GOOD SUMMARY I HAVE NO
REASON TO BELIEVE IT.
HE READ IT.
HE DIDN'T OBJECT TO IT.
IENT OVER THIS LETTER IN GREAT
DETAIL.
THE ONLY THING WE HAVE ANY ISSUE
WITH IS THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
PUNTING THE DECISION ON
OBSTRUCTION TO THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL.
I THINK HE SHOULD HAVE MADE THAT
DECISION.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE AGREE WITH
YOU ON THAT.
HE SHOULD HAVE MADE A SPECIFIC
RECOMMENDATION.
>> ALSO, REMEMBER, THIS ALSO
DOES NOTRATE HIM.
>> I WILL GET TO THAT IN A
MOMENT.
>> THAT'S KIND OF CLOSE TO AN
IMPROPER STATEMENT.
>> THE ATTORNEY GENERAL IN HIS
LETTER, THE FOUR-PAGE LETTER
QUOTES MUELLER AS SAYING THAT
THE INVESTIGATION I'M QUOTING
FROM THE LETTER DID NOT
ESTABLISH THAT MEMBER OF THE
TRUMP CAMPAIGN COORDINATED WITH
THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT.
SO IS THERE AN INNOCENT
EXPLANATION WHY SO MANY TRUMP
ASSOCIATES WERE MEETING WITH
RUSSIANS DURING THE CAMPA
>> IT WASN'T THATR MANY -- HE
PLEADED GUILTY.
HI LIED ABOUT INTERACTIONS WHO
HAD TIES TO RUSSIAN
INTELLIGENCE.
ALL OF THESE PEOPLE LIED ABOUT
RUSSIAN CONTEXT.
NONE OF THEM WENT TO THE FBI AND
REPORTED THE CONTEXT OF THE FBI.
>> AT THE TIME THAT IT■ HAPPENE.
>> TIME OUT.
>> ISN'T THAT SOMETHING YOU
SHOULD TELL THE DPRFBI ABOUT?
>> IF YOU BELIEVE IT WAS ABOUT
SANCTIONS, RIGHT AND HE FAILED
TO DISCLOSE THAT AND HE MISLEAD
THE VICE PRESIDENT.
IT HAD NOTHING TOITH■
INFORM ON?=?m HILLARY.
SO IT TOOK PLACE AFTER THE
ELECTION.
SO WHETHER HE TOLD THE TRUTH OR
DIDN'T TELL THE TRUTH GOT
NOTHING TO DO WITH?■LUSION.
SO ONCE AGAIN MULTIPLE OFFERS TO
ASSIST THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN DOES
IT REGRET THAT HIS ASSOCIATES
AFTER GETTING THOSE OFFERS NEVER
REPORTED THOSE CONTACTS TO THE
FBI.
>> I CAN'T SAY WHETHER HE DOES
ORC DOESN'T.
YOU SAY WE HAVE INFORMATION THAT
IS DAMAGING TO HILLARY CLINTON.
THERE IS INFORMATION THAT WILL
HELP DONALD TRUMP SHOULDN'T THEY
NOTIFY THE FBI OF THAT?
>> I WOULD SAY WHAT YOU'RE DOING
IS MISSING THE FOREST THROUGH
THE TREES.
SPECIAL COUNSEL DID NOT --
>> BUT --
>> LET ME READ IT.
>> DID IN THE CONSPIRE DESPITE
MULTIPLE EFFORTS --
>> I AGREE.
>> THAT'S THE HEADLINE.
>> THE HEADLINE THEY DID NOT
CONSPIRE OR KOOR DIN FLAT.
THE QUESTION IS WHAT ABOUT ALL
OF THE MULTIPLE EFFORTS BY
RUSSIAN OFFICIALS TO TRY TO MEET
WITH THESE --
>> I GUESS THEY ANTICIPATED WHAT
IS GOING TO HAPPEN OR HAVE
DETAILED KNOWLEDGE OF THE LAW.
>> WHAT YOULD HAVE DONE IF
DURING THE CAMPAIGN AND YOU
WERE --
>> I HAPPENED TO BE A LAWYER.
>> WHAT YOULD WOULD YOU DONE IF
A RUSSIAN SAID I WILL HELP
THE -- WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE DONE?
>> I WOULD HAVE REPORTEDER
BECAUSE I KNEW IT COULD BE A
VIOLATION OF THE LAW.
IT GETS YOU INTO A WHOLE
DISCUSSION OF IS IT A CAMPAIGN
CONTRIBUTION OR NOT?
OUT OF AN EXCESS OF CAUTION, IF
YOU CAME TO ME OR SOMEBODY ON
THE CAMPAIGN CAME TO ME AND SAID
ASIAN OFFICIAL OFFERED
DIFFERENTY INFORMATION ON
HILLARY, NOW, YOU DON'T STRICTLY
HAVE TO DO IT.
NOTHING ILLEGAL ABOUT REPORTING
A CRIME.
NUMBER TWO, THIS IS ARGUABLY A
CRIME.
A BIG DEBATE AS TO WHETHER OR
NOT INFORMATION FROM A FOREIGNER
IS A CONTRIBUTION TO THE
CAMPAIGN.
SOME LAWYERS SAY YES.
SOME LAW;b;&AY NO.
THE VUE OF IT?
DOES IT HAVE A MONETARY VALUE?
HELL OF A RUSH.
NO STRICT DUTY TO REPORT.
I GUARANTEE YOU MOST OF THESE
PEOPLE VA HEARD ME, THEY
WOULDN'T HAVE KNOWN IT'S A
VIOLATION OF THE LAW.
THEY WOULD HAVE HAD NO IDEA THAT
A FREFRM PERSON SAYS I GOT DIRTY
INFORMATION ON TRUMP OR HILLARY
THAT IS IT A POSSIBLE VIOLATION
OF THE LAW.
PLEASE, I REALLY BELIEVE IT IS A
SMALL POINT IN LIKE OF THE FACT
THAT FOR TWO NAR YEARS HE LIED.
>> LET'S GET TO THE ISSUE OF
ZBLP IT BEGAN BECAUSISH SHA WAS
TRYING TO BER HE SAID RUSSIANS
HAD INFORMATION.
>> MAP IT WILL TURN OUT.
IT MAY NOT BE CORRECT.
>> DO YOU BETTER INFORMATION?
>> I DO BUT I'M NOT AT LYNNERTY
TO KIS THOSE IT LAST NIGHT.
IT WAS THE US A TRAIL DWRANS
THAT WED.
I HAVE NO KNOWLEDGE OF ANY
HACKING M IT IS LEFT OAT TO BE
DFRP HE WROTE AN EXPERT REPORT
ON RUSSIA.
HADN'T BEEN THERE FOR NINE
YEARS.
NOBODY TOLD THE JUDGE HE GOT
FIRED.
FLOEB TOLD ANYBODY AT THE
DOSSIER SHE PAID $1.1 MILLION TO
HAVE IT.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS.
HE SAYS THIS REPORT BASED ON THE
SUMMARY ALL OF US HAVE READ IS A
COMPLETE AND TOTAL EXONERATION.
THIS IS WHAT THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL QUOTES MUELLER AS SAYING
WHILE IT DOES NOT CONCLUDE IT
ALSO DOES NOT EXONERATE.
IS THE PRESIDENT FRUSTRATED BY
THAT ONE LINE QUOTED IN THIS
DOCUMENT?
>> NO.
I THINK THE PRESIDENT IS SAYING
YOU READ THIS LETTER AND NEXT
PARAGRAPH OF THE LETTER RIGHT
AFTER THIS THIS DECISION ABOUT
IS IT A CRIME OR IS IT ANOTHER
CRIME WAS TO THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL TO ROSEN STEIN.
I UNDERSTAND ALTHOUGH I DON'T
HAVE DETAILED KNOWLEDGE OF THIS
THEY TOOK TWO TO THREE WEEKS.
>> THREE WEEKS.
>> THAT'S ABOUT RIGHT THEY GAVE
IT TO --
>> OFF OF THE LEGAL COUNSEL OR
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT.
THEY REVIEWED EVERY CASE ON
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE AND CAME
TO THIS CONCLUSION.
IT EXONERATES IT.
I GUESS YOU WOULD HAVE TO SAY
MUELLER AND BAR EXONERATED HIM
ON COLLUSION AND THE ATTY
OBSTRUCTION NOT MUELLER.
MUELLER I CAN'T SAY IT'S A
CRIME BUT I CAN'T EXONERATE.
THIS IS ABOUT AS GOOD AS A
DECLINATION.
>> THEY SAID HE IS ON HONORABLE
GUY.
MAYBE THE GUY WAS CONFUSED AND
HE PUNTED HIM.
I HAVE A GUESS AS TO WHAT
HAPPENED.
I THINK HIS STAFF WAS AND AS A
QUESTION.
>> BUT YOU KNOW ROBERT MUELLER.
>> YES.
>> AND I SIDE FROM THE CRITICISM
I GAVE YOU BEFORE I HAVE A GOOD
VIEW OF HIM.
EVERYBODY MAKES MISTAKES.
>> HE WOULDN'T MAKE UP HIS OWN
MIND?
>> HE SAYS -- I MEAN I IMAGINE
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL DESCRIBED
WHAT THE SPECIAL COUNCIL VIEWS
AS.HERS SUGGESTED HE WAS TO
DECIDE WHETHER THE PRESIDENT DID
ANYTHING.
>> HE STILL GOT A LAWYER NOT
REALIZED IT WAS THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL'S POSITION.
SO HE DIDN'T ACTUALLY CHARGE IT
FROM THE ATTORNEY GENERAL.
ALSO FROM THE IDEA HE REPORTED
IT THREE WEEKS EARLIER I THINK
HE NIGH THAT IT WOULD BE A
REVIEW.
>> YOU DON'T FLOW FOR SURE THAT
MUELLER WANTED THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL TO MAKE A FINAL
DECISION.
I DO THINK HE WOULD NOT HAVE
REPORTED THREE WEEKS EAR
>> YOU W THIS WHOLE MUELLER
REPORT TO BE RELEASED WITH THE
EXCLUSION OF SOME GRAND JURY
TESTIMONY OR NATIONAL SECURITY
SECRETS CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
YOU WANT IT TO BE RELEASED WHEN?
>> CONSISTENT WITH THE LAW
KNOWING HOW LONG IT IS REPORTED
TO BE.
>> AND IF THEY WANT TO PUT OUT
GRAND JURY MATERIAL THEY CAN GO
TO A JUDGE AND GET IT.
THEY MIGHT NOT GET IT BUT THEY
CAN TRTO DO IT.
>> IF THE PRESIDENT HAD NOTHING
TO HIDE WHY WEREN'T YOU WILLING
TO LETIM SIT DOWN FOR AN
INTERVIEW SPECIAL COUNS>■■■■■>■
WRITING BUT HE NEVER AGREED TO
SIT DOWN AND TALK ABOUT IT.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GET SUED FOR
MALPRACTICE.
I WOULD BE A HELD OF AN AWFUL
LAWYER IF I WALKED HIM IN WHERE
I HAD EVERY REASON TO BELIEVE
THEY WEREN'T IN GOOD FAITH.
THEY WERE GOING TO TRY TO TRAP
HIM WITH COHEN LYING HIS WHAT
OFF.
I'M NOT ARGUING HE THE
TRUTH OR DIDN'T TELL HIM.
TH?I?I TRAPP?I■I■I■I HIM.
THEY HAD EVERYTHING.
THEY ASKED HIM DID YOU HAVE ANY
MEETI
MEETINGS.
THEY ASKED THE QUESTION.
HE SAID I DON'T REMEMBER A
MEETING LIKE THAT.
IF YOU DO THAT YOU TAKE THE MEMO
OUT AND YOU SAY LOOK, YOU HAD A
MEETING.
DOES THAT REFRESH YOUR
RECKLATR
RECOLLECTION ABOUT THAT MEETING?
YOU KEEP IT IN THE DESK.
WHEN IT COMES NEXT TO THAT YOU
SAY PERJURY.
WE ALSO KNOW SOME OF THE FBI
AGENTS DIDN'T THINK HE LIED
ABOUT IT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW IT ALL SWITCHED
INTO CHARGING IT.
>> I TAKE IT IN THE Q AND A YOU
DIDN'T WANT THE PRESIDENT TO
ANSWER ANY QUESTIONS INVOLVING
OBSTRUCTION, IS THAT RIGHT?
>> A COUPLE REASONS FOR THAT.
NUMBER ONE THE PRIVILEGE THAT HE
HAS, THE EXECUTIVE PREF LIJ THAT
HE HAS IS MUCH STRONGER FROM THE
DAY HE IS ELECTED PRESIDENT.
SO JUST CONVENIENTLY DIVIDED
INTO THE COLLUSION, ALLEGED
COLLUSN ALL TOOK PLACE BEFORE
HE WAS PRESIDENT.
>> A PRIVATE CITIZEN.
>> WE COULD HAVE MADE A CLAIM OF
PRIVILEGE.
OUR CHANCESO OF WINNING THAT
WOULD BE BETTER THAN OURS.
TON OTHER HAND FROM THE DAY HE
BECOMES PRESIDENT AND THE DAY HE
IS INAUGURATED IT BECOMES VERY
STRONG.
HE DOESN'T ONLY BECOME STRONG IT
IS BECAUSE OF WHAT THEY DID.
BY TURNING OVER 1.4 MILLION
DOCUMENTS BY NOT OBJECTING TO 50
WITNESSES, REMEMBER BILL CLINTON
OBJECTED TO WITNESSES MADE IT
HARDER FOR HIM TO ASSERT
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE.
HE GOT INDICTED FOR PERJURY.
THEY SAT HIM DOWN FOR AN
INTERVIEW.
IT IS KIND OF ON OUR MIND.
SO I'M A LAWYER.
I'M NOT A POLITICIAN.
I AM A POLITICIAN.
IN THIS ROLE I'M A LAWYER.
MY JOB IS TO PROTECT MY CLIENT.
IF HE WEREN'T THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES THERE WOULD BE
NO CONSIDERATION AT ALL.
MOST PEOPLE UNDER INVESTIGATION
DO NOT GO INTO A GRAND JURY OR
TESTIFY UNDER OATH.
EVERY ONE I MADE I DIDN'T HAVE
THE BENEFIT.
>> AND YOU CAN RELAEASE ON YOUR
OWN Q AND A WHAT HE DID WITH
MUELLER.
>> WHEN YOU RELEASE IT ASSUMING
THEY DON'T WANT TO RELEASE IT DO
YOU A PROBLEM RELEASING THAT?
>> THE ANSWERS ARE ALL TRUTHFUL
OTHERWISE YOU WOULD HAVE SEEN
IT.
>> WE WOULD LOVE TO HAVE SEEN
WHAT THE SPECIAL COUNSEL ASKS
AND WHAT THE PRESIDENT SAID.
I ASSUME YOU WORKED REALLY HARD
TO WRITE THE ANSWERS.
>> HE GAVE THE ANSWERS AND WE
WORKED REALLY HARD TO MAKE SURE
HIS RECOLLECTION WAS CORRECT.
YOU LOOKED AT THE DOCUMENTS YOU
HAVE TO LOOK AT WHICH WOULDN'T
HAVE HAPPENED IN A SITUATION
WHERE THEY ARE TRYING TO TRAP
IT.
>> AND SO YOU CAN ASSURE US?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> BUT UP TO YOU YOU WOULD
RELEASE IT?
>> NOTHING IN THERE I HAVE ANY
PROBLEM WITH.
I THINK YOU KNOW MOST OF THE
ANSWERS THAT ARE IN THERE.
>> WE WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED SM.
>> NO SURPRISE.
>> HOW MANY PAGES WAS IT?
>> THE QUESTIONS WERE ABOUT
RECOLLECTION NOW BACK THEN SEVEN
OR EIGHT PAGES OF QUESTIONS.
THEY HAD A TOPIC AND THEN HAD
EIGHT SUB QUESTIONS.
THEN OUR ANSWERS THEN GO IN
SEQUENCE WITH THOSE.
SO MAYBE OUR WE VENN CLUL
ANSWERS AT 15O 20 PAGES.
>> YOU TOLD MY COLLEAGUE YOU
HAVE A 97 PAGE REBUTTAL READY TO
BE RELEASED.
>> 87.
>> CAN YOU GIVE US A SENSE OF
WHAT IS THERE T REPORT?
>> YEAH.
LET'S TALK ABOUT OBSTRUCTION.
IT GOES ON -- IT GOES INTO WHY
THIS COULD NOT BE AN OBSTRUCTION
ON MANY DIFFERENT LEVELS.
ONE OF THE THINGS THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL PICKS UP ON THERE WAS NO
UNDERLYING CRIME BY EXONERATING
HIM ON COLLUSION IT TURNS OUT
THEY ARE NOT --
>> PEOPLE GO TO JAIL EVEN THOUGH
THEY DIDN'T COMMIT A CRIME.
>> YOU LIED ABOUT IT.
>> THE ATTORNEY GENERAL SAYS IT
IS HARD TO FIND INTENT.
YOU CAN.
>> SHE DIDN'T ENGAGE THERE
INSIDER TRADING BUT SHE WOUND UP
IN JAIL BECAUSE SHE LIED ABOUT
IT.
>> ALTHOUGH THERE WAS A VERY
CLOSE CASE INVOLVING MARTHA
STEWART, A QUESTION OF FACT AS
WHO WAS TELLING THE TRUTH AND
WHO WASN'T.
IN THIS CASE THERE IS NO CASE OF
COLLUS
COLLUSION.
THAT'S NOT THE ONLY THING.
SECOND, THERE IS NONE OF THE
THINGS THAT YOU USUALLY HAVE
WITH AN OBSTRUCTION CASE.
LET'S TAKE THE FLYNN SITUATION
WHICH HE SAYS DIDN'T TAKE PLACE.
IF YOU TAKE HIS TESTIMONY HE
SAYS THE PRESIDENT SAID TO ME GO
EASY ON FLYNN.
THAT'S OBSTRUCTION.
I NEVER HEARD OF OBSTRUCTION
CASE.
I THINK IT BEGAN WITH PLEAS.
YOU NEVER START WITH PLEAS.
IT STARTS WITH TAKE YOUR MONEY
AWAY.
SOME THREAT INVOLVED IN IT.
SOME KIND OF COERCION.
FINALLY IT COULDN'T BE
OBSTRUCTION BECAUSE ASSUMING HE
IS TELLING THE TRUTH, SO WHAT
HAPPENED THERE MAY YOU FIGURED
OUT HE WAS OBSTRUCTED IN
FEBRUARY.
I'M GOING TO REPORT IT TO THE
FBI?
I THINK WE WILL KILL THAT
OBSTRUCTION THEORY.
>> WERE YOU SURPRISED?
>> I DESCRIBE IT AS A VERY VERY
OFFICIAL LEGAL TERM.
I DESCRIBE IT AS A LEGAL THEORY
OF OBSTRUCTION.
>> WERE YOU SURPRISED MUELLER
AND HIS TEAM DIDN'T SUBPOENA THE
PRESIDENT TO SEEK AN ORAL B
INTERVIEW?
>> YOU WERE BRACING FOR THAT
RIGHT?
>> WE COULD HAVE.■v I TOLD YOU,
OBSTRUCTION PART AFTER HE WAS
PRESIDENT I THINK WE HAD THE
BETTER ARGUMENT.
I THINK WE WOULD HAVE WON THAT
BATTLE PARTICULARLY BECAUSE WE
HAD SO MUCH INFORMATION.
WHAT YOU TO SHOW FLORD GET ■A
PRESIDENT'S TESTIMONY HE TRIED
TO RESIST THE SUBPOENA.
HE LOST.
THE COURT SAID YOU HAVE TO SHOW
IF YOU WANT TO SUBPOENA A
PRESIDENT THAT YOU CAN'T GET
THIS INFORMATION ANY OTHER WAY.
WE WERE PRETTY CONFIDENT
WHATEVSTIONSY WANTED ■@■@■@HEY
INFORMATION WHICH IS ALSO WHY
THEY SUSPECTED THEY WERE TRYING
TO TRAP HIM IN THE PERJURY.
WE DIDN'T NEED HIS EXPLANATIONS.
>> WHY DID HE FIRE COMEY?
>> HE GAVE ALL OF THE REASONS.
HE IS GOING TO REPEAT IT.
>> LET ME MENTION RUSSIA?
>>NO QUESTION RUSSIA HAD
SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT.
THERE WERE EIGHT OTHER REASONS
CHLS THAT ALL HE NEEDS.
HE HAD VERY VERY GOOD REASONS TO
FIRE HIM.
HILLARY WOULD HAVE FIRED THE GUY
I THINK.
>> WELL, HILLARY WOULD HAVE
FIRED HIM FOR OTHER REASONS.
>> COCOMEY DID NOT COVER
HIMSELF.
>> I HIRED JIM COMEY.
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T FLOW WHAT HAPPENED TO
HIM.
HE DID NOT COVER HIMSELF WITH
GLORY MANY THIS PARTICULAR CASE.
WHAT HE DID TO HILLARY CLINTON
IS WRONG.
YOU DON'T SAY I'M NOT GOING TO
INDICT AND THEN SAY ALL OF THE
BAD THINGS ABOUT SOMEBODY AND
YOU DON'T SAY I'M NOT GOING TO
INDICT BUT SAY I CAN'T
EXONERATE.
>> WAS THERE --
>> THAT'S A CLHEAP SHOT.
>> WAS THERE EVER A THOUGHT THAT
MUELLER WAS GOING TO ASK HIM TO
TESTIFY?
>> NO.
THERE WAS NEVER -- THAT NEVER
CAME UP.
SO WE NEVER FACED THE SITUATION.
WHAT DID HAPPEN PERSISTENTLY,
AND YOU HEARD SOME OF THESE,
THERE WERE RUMORS AND THEN WE
CHECK AND YOU GET ONE ABOUT
THREE OR FOUR WEEKS.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT THEY WERE TO
GET THE PRESIDENT ANGRY.
I CAN TELL YOU THE PRESIDENT
HANDLED THE STUFF AGAINST HIM
REALLY WELL.
THE PRESIDENT WOULD GET UPSET
WHEN IT INVOLVED HIS FAMILY OR
SOME OF THE PEOPLE THAT WORKED
FOR HIM OR SOME OF THE KIDS LIKE
SOME OF THESE PEOPLE YOU SEE ON
TELEVISION HAD TO SPEND AN
ENORMOUS AMOUNT OF MONEY.
>> AND IN THAT TRUMP TOWER
MEETING IN JUNE OF 2016 WHEN
THEY MET WITH THIS RUSSIAN THAT
SUPPOSEDLY.
HE SAID GREAT.
WE'LL TAKE IT.
>> JARED WAS IN ABOUT HALF OF
THE MEETING.
>> WERE YOU SURPRISED HAY DIDN'T
CALL ON THEM TO AT LEAST ANSWER
QUESTIONS?
>> I'M NOT SURPRISED BECAUSE I
THINK FROM THE PEOPLE ON THE
OTHER SIDE OF THAT MEETING I
DON'T THINK THEY EVER DISCUSSED
HILLARY CLINTON.
SO IT GOT SET UP THAT WAY BUT IT
REALLY WAS A PRETEXT TO TALK
ABOUT ADOPTIONS AND ADOPTIONS
FROM RUSSIA AND SO EVERYBODY
KIND OF WALKED OUT ON■P■  IT.
>> YOUR THOUGHTS ON GRAHAM
SAYING IT WAS HIS IDEA TO HAND
OVER THE DOSSIER TO THE FBI.
YOU HE SAY IT A LITTLE
WHILE AGO.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN REALLY
RAILING AGAINST THE LATE SENATOR
JOHN McCAIN BLAMING HIM FOR THIS
WHOLE THING.
GRAHAM SAYS I SUGGESTED TO H
HIMTH
HIM THERE'S A LOT OF DIRT IN
THERE.
>> I HAVEN'T READ ALL OF IT.
I READ A LOT OF WHAT'S IN THERE.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE SAW IT.
HE MAY HAVE BEEN DESCRIBED TO
HIM.
I THINK HE HAS A PROFESSIONAL
LAWYER WOULD REALIZE IT'S A
PIECE OF GARBAGE.
IT'S A SILLY DOCUMENT.
IT'S NOT A WELL WRITTEN
INTELLIGENCE DOCUMENT.
IT IS OBVIOUSLY -- IT LOOKS LIKE
A BIG LONG NATIONAL INQUIRER
ARTICLE.
IT DOESN'T SEEM TO COME FROM AN
INTEL
INTELLIGENCE PROFESSIONAL.
THE RUSSIANS MADE HIM AN AGENT
TEN YEARS AGO AND DECIDED FIVE
YEARS AGO HE WOULD BE PRESIDENT.
IF THEY COULD FIGUR OUT HE
WOULD BE PRESIDENT THEY WILL BE
IN A LOT OF TROUBLE.
THEY ARE A LOT SMARTER THAN THEY
THINK THEY ARE.
>> AND OTHER --
>> THERE IS ALSO ANOTHER THING
THEY DID WITH THAT THAT'S REALLY
THERE'S A SPECIFIC ALLEGATION IN
THERE THAT MICHAEL COHEN WENT TO
GET INFORMATION FOR THE
RUSSIANS.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL YOU TO DO IS THE DATE.
CALL THE STATE DEPARTMENT AND
FIND OUT WHAT DOES THIS PASSPORT
SAY?
THEY ARE DOING THIS
EXTRAORDINARY ACT.
A MAN TURNS OUT TO BE INNOCENT.
THEY DON'T EVEN BOTHER TO CHECK
THE ONE THING.
>> YOU KNOW TO SOUTHERN DISTRICT
OF NEW YORK.
YOU ONCE WERE THE U.S. ATTORNEY,
THEY ARE PRETTY AGGRESS IFR.
HOW WORRIED ARE YOU THAT THE
MUELLER INFORMATION 22 MONTHS IS
OVER WITH NOW BUT THEIR
INVESTIGATION FROM SOME FROM
SOME PERSPECTIVE IS ONLY JUST
BEGINNING.
>> IT HAS BEEN GOING ON BEFORE
THE SUMMER.
>> I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT IT AT
ALL.
THERE'S NO VIOLATION OF THE LAW.
WHEN YOU MAKE PAYMENTS TO SETTLE
PERSONAL CLAIM AND FEEVEN IF IT
HELPS IT CAN'T POSSIBLY BE A
CAMPAIGN CONTRIBUTION.
IT IS A VERY FAULTY LEGAL
THEORY.
>> THEY SITED IT AS A CAMPAIGN
CONTRIBUTION, THE MONEY THAT WAS
GIVEN.
>> LET THEM TRY TO INCITE
SOMEBODY.
THE COURT WILL THROW IT OUT.
>> HE PLEADED GUILTY.
IF IT CAN BE CONSIDERED A
CAMPAIGN CONTRIBUTION THECHB I
CAN RUN FOR OFFICE NOW.
I CAN SETTLE EVERY CASE AGAINST
ME AND USE MY DONORS MONEY TO DO
IT AND THEY WOULD PUT ME IN
JAIL.
THAT'S THE THEORY THEY HAVE AND
IT WILL FALL DOWN.
YOU NOTICED IN THAT DOCUMENT, IN
THAT CHARGE AGAINST MICHAEL
COHEN AND THE JUDGE ACCEPTED IT
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES IS IDENTIFIED AS
INDIVIDUAL NUMBER ONE.
>> WHETHER IT IS OR ISN'T IT'S
NOT A CRIME.
IF IT'S A CRIME THEN WE HAVE 30
PLUS MEMBERS OF CONGRESS WHO
OVER THE LAST SEVER YEARS HAVE
HAD CLAI CLAIMS OF SEXUAL HARAS.
>> DID THE PRESIDENT DO THAT?
>> WHAT?
>> WORK TO PAY OFF --
>> I'M NOT SAYING HE DID.
I'M TELLING YOU IF THEY TRY TO
ALLEGE THAT AS A CRIME IT IS IN
THE A CRIME.
HE WOULD HAVE A WEIRD SUCH WAYS
PEOPLE WOULD RUN TO CLEAN OUT
ALL OF THE CLIMBS AGAINST HIM
AND USE DONORS MONEY TO DO THAT.
IT WOULD BE AN ABACCIDENT
OCCURRED ABSURD APPLICATION.
>> AND YOU KNOW THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL, YOUR HOME STATEOVER NEW
YORK, THE STATE ATTORNEY
GENERAL, INVESTIGATING AND
SHE IS INVESTIGATING.
>> SHE RAN ON THE PLATFORM THAT
I'M GOING TO INVESTIGATE DONALD
TRUMP AND I'M GOING TO GET HIM
FOR SOMETHING.
VERY CREDIBLE.
>> SO YOU'RE NOT WORRIED
ABOUT --
>> SHE IS LOOKING AT THE
FOUNDATION.
HE PAID OUT 19 MILLION AND HE
RAISED ONLY 18 MILLION.
HE DONATED ABOUT 18 MILLION OF
HIS OWN MINUTE.
THERE'S NOT A SINGLE CLAIM THAT
NOBODY WAS PAID.
NO BIG SALARIES.
NO TRIPS PAID FOR.
NO PERKS, NOT $150 MILLION
CONTRIBUTION FROM RUSSIA LIKEE .
I DON'T THINK THERE'S A PROBLEM.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT
INVESTIGATING THE TRUMP
ORGANIZATION?
>> NO BECAUSE I THINK THE TRUMP
ORGANIZATION IS CLEAN.
IT'S A CLEAN ORGANIZATION.
SHEER WHAT I REALLY WORRY ABOUT
AS A CITIZEN.
THIS IS LIKE SAYING I'M GOING TO
GO BACK IN THIS MAN'S LIFER I'M
GOING TO GO BACK AND FIND
SOMETHING HE DID WRONG.
SO I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG IS THAT
GOING GO■á ON?
>> ARE YOU GOING TO STICK AROUND
AND CONTINUE THIS?
WHAT'S THE NEXT CLAP TER.
>> I DO A LOT OF OTHER THINGS.
I RUN A SECURITY BUSINESS AND WE
DO SECURITY CONSULTING.
>> I HEARD ON STRATEGISTS THAT
SAY HE DOESN'T THINK IT IS WISE
TO PURSUE IMPEACHMENTS.
>> JIM IS IN THE HOUSE --
>> SAY THAT --
>> HE SAID WE HAVE TO MOVE ON
THIS CHAPTER IS OVER WITH.
>> SHE HAD THE RIGHT STANDARD
POLITICALLY WHICH IS YOU HAVE TO
HAVE BIPARTISAN SUPPORT.
IF YOU DON'T IT WILL LOOK LIKE A
COMPLETELY POLITICAL WITCH HUNT.
I DON'T THINK YOU'LL GET
BIPARTISAN SUPPORT BASED ON
THIS.
I HAVE A PRETTY GOOD IDEA FOR
THE REST OF WHAT THEY HAVE.
>> LOOKING FORWARD TO GETTING A
FULL REPORT.
>> IF ANYTHING IS ELD BACK I
KNOW SOMEONE WILL SAY OH, MY
GOD.
>> I WOULD LIKE THE WHOLE TLING
TO BE OUT.
>> I'M SURE THE PRESIDENT IS
GRATEFUL FOR YOU.
>> I'M GRATEFUL THAT HOWEVER
THEY GOT THERE WRONG OR NOT
WRONG I'M GRATEFUL THAT AN
INNOCENT MAN WAS, YOU KNOW,
VINDICATED.
>> AND YOU'RE ALWAYS WELCOME TO
COME BACK INTO OUR SITUATION
ROOM.
HAVE YOU BEEN TO THE WHITE HOUSE
SITUATION ROOM?
>> YEAH.
>> I WAS IN RE BEGAN
ADMINISTRATION.
I GO WAY BACK ALMOST AS OLD AS
YOU.
>>■R MAYBE.
>> THANKS SO MUCH FOR COMING
OUT.
APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WE'LL HAVE A LOT MORE COMING
UP RIGHT AFTER THIS.
■■,
If you have postmenopausal
osteoporosis
and a high risk for fracture
now might not be the best time
to ask yourself
are my bones strong?
Life is full of make-or-break
moments.
That's why it's so importantçT
and protect bones from fracture
with 1 shot every 6 months.
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take
XGEVA®.
Serious allergic reactions,
like low blood pressure; trouble
breathing;
throat tightness; face, lip, or
tongue swelling;
rash; itching; or hives have
happened.
Tell your doctor about denta■■■
as severe jaw bone problems may
happen
or new or unusual pain in your
hip groin, or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone fractures
urred.
Speak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects,
like low blood calcium, serious
infections,
which could need
hospitalization, skin problems,
and severe bone, joint, or
muscle pain.
Are you ready?
Ask your doctor how Prolia® can
help strengthen your bones.
>>> JUSTICE DEPARTMENT SAID IT
WILL TAKE WEEKS FOR BILL BARR TO
MAKE A VERSION OF THE MUELLER
REPORT AVAILABLE.
I JUST SPOKE AT LENG WITH RUDY
GIULIANI.
WE HAVE A LOT TO DISCUSS.
SUSAN, LET ME GET YOUR THOUGHTS
ON WHAT WE JUST HEARD FROM THE
MAYOR.
>> IT IS DIFFICULT SO PARSE IT
ALL OUT.
AGAIN, THE BAR SUMMARY IS NOT
THE MUELLER REPORT.
APPARENTLY THE WHITE HOUSE HAS
NOT REVIEWED THE MUELLER REPORT
FOR THEMSELVES SO THEY ARE
MAKING -- OPERATING WITH SAME
INFORMATION WE ARE.
IN IT DOES NOT EXONERATE THE
PRESIDENT OR ANSWER SERIOUS
QUESTIONS ABOUT HIS CAMPAIGN'S
CONDUCT.
IT IS INTERESTING THAT JEWGIULI
ADMITTED HAD A RUSSIAN
INDIVIDUAL REACHED OUT THAT HE
WOULD HAVE BEEN INCLINED TO
CONTACT THE FBI.
I THINK IT GOES TO ONE OF THE
CORE QUESTIONS HERE WHICH IS
ROBERT MUELLER HAS NOW ANSWERED
THE QUESTION ABOUT WHETHER OR
NOT ANY CRIMINAL CONDUCT
OCCURRED.
I DOESN'T MEAN THAT UNACCEPTABLE
NOW WE'LL HAVE TO DECIDE IF WHAT
THE PRESIDENT DID WAS ACCEPTABLE
OR NOT.
ZB HE SAID HE WANTS EVERYTHING
RELEASED.
HE SAID IMPLIED YOU
RELEASE GRAND JURY TESTIMONY IF
YOU GET A JUDGE TO SAY OKAY.
WHAT WAS
HIS DESCRIPTION OF THE WRITTEN
QUESTIONS AND HOW THERE WERE
MULTIPLE PAGES, SEVEN OR EIGHT
OR WHATEVER IT WAS WITH SUB
TEXT.
WHEN YOU ASKED HIM WHY DIDN'T
YOU HAVE THE PRESIDENT TESTIFY
IF HE'S TELLING THE TRUTH, HE
SAID IT WOULD BE MALPRACTICE.
AND THAT IS OUR UNDERSTANDING OF
WHAT THE LAWYERS■& SAYING.
WHICH THEY WOULD LAY THEMSELVES
DOWN IN FRONT OF A BUS BEFORE
THEY'D LET DONALD TRUMP TESTIFY.
BUT I MUST SAY THIS IS SORT OF
THE FOR ME IN HEARING RUDY
GIULIANI, IT'S THE CALMEST I
HAVE EVER HEARD HIM ABOUT THIS
ENTIRE CASE BECAUSE THE RELIEF
IS PALPABLE FOR HIM.
I DO BELIEVE THE PRESIDENT IS
MISCHARACTERIZED THE
EXONERATION, OR SO-CALLED
EXONERATION OR ON OBSTRUCTION,
WHICH THERE WAS NONE, BUT YOU
CAN SEE THAT THE RELIEF IS
THERE.
AND THAT HE SAYS YET AGAIN, PUT
EVERYTHING OUT THERE.
IF HE'S SAYING PUT EVERYTHING
OUT THERE AND THE CONGRESS IS
SAYING PUT EVERYTHING OUT THERE
AND THE PRESIDENT IS SAYING PUT
VRG OUT THERE, WHY NOT?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I THINK THE RELIEF COULD BE
SHORT LIVED.
THE MUELLER REPORT, AS WE
UNDERSTAND IT, TO THE DEGREE
THAT IF FOUND THERE WAS NO
INSTITUTIONAL LEVEL CONSPIRACY
BETWEEN THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND
THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT, THE
PRESIDENT IS CLEAR.
BUT AS SUSAN POINTED OUT, WHAT
WE DON'T KNOW IS THE EXTENT TO
WHICH INDIVIDUALS ON THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGNEN ENGAGED IN ACTIVITIES
WITH RUSSIAN OFFICIALS THAT MAY
NOT HAVE RISEN TO THE LEVEL OF
CRIMINALITY, BUT STILL
COMPLETELY INAPPROPRIATE.
SO THAT'S A QUESTION THAT MUST
BE ANSWERED.
WE HAVE AN ISSUE OF OBSTRUCTION
OF JUSTICE.
WE DON'T KNOW THAT THE PRESIDENT
NEVER OBSTRUCTED JUSTICE IS
BASED ON PREEXISTING NOTION■  TT
A PRESIDENT CAN'T BE GUILTY OR
IF IT WAS BASED ON A WELCOME OF
EVIDENCE AND ONLY THE REPORT
WILL HELP US UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> THE MAYOR RUDY GIULIANI SAID
HE WOULD BE FINE RELEASING THE
WRITTEN Q&A THE PRESIDENT
ENGAGED IN WITH ROBERT MUELLER.
HE WOULDN'T HAVE IS A PROBLEM.
>> HE SAID HE WANTS IT ALL OUT
THERE.
WHAT'S INTERESTING IS HIS
CHARACTER RAIGS.
THE PRESIDENT WAS ASKED IF HE
THOUGHT HE WAS AN HONORABLE MAN
AND HE SAID YES.
RUDY GIULIANI SAID HE DISAGREED
WITH THE PRESIDENT AND SAID HE
WASN'T HONORABLE AT LEAST IN HOW
HE HANDLED THIS INVESTIGATION.
AND ALSO I THOUGHT IT WAS
STRIKING THAT HE SAID THAT
ROBERT MUELLER MAY HAVE BEEN
CONFUSED WHEN TRY ING TO DECIDE
ON WHETHER THE PRESIDENT
OBSTRUCTED JUSTICE AND THAT'S
WHY IN HIS WORDS HE PUNTED.
AND THEN HE REALLY DID GO AFTER
PROSECUTION AS WELL.
SOME OF THE OTHER PROSECUTORS
THERE, CALLING HIM MUELLER'S
HENCHMAN AND THEN THE OTHER
THING THAT STRUCK ME WAS WHEN
YOU ASKED ABOUT A PARDON FOR
MANAFORT AND HE MAY HAVE
COMMITTED A CRIME BUT DOESN'T DO
SOMETHING SO EGREGIOUS TO BE
TREATED THE WAY HE WAS.
>> IT'S INTERESTING.
THE FULL ISSUE OF PARDONS, HE
SAID MANAFORT WAS TREATED
UNFAIRLY BY THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
AND MICHAEL FLYNN, THE FORMER
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER WAS
BADLY TREATED AS WELL.
>> BUT HE SAID■ WE HAVEN'T
DISCUSSED PARDONS.
M
IT'S THE COUNSEL'S JOB IN THE
WHITE HOUSE.
HE'S RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
BUT WHAT WAS INTERESTING TO ME
IS IT'S CLEAR THAT WHAT STICKS
IN THE PRESIDENT'S CRAW AND RUDY
GIULIANI IS IS THE LINE THAT
SAYS THAT WE CAN'T CONCLUDE THE
PRESIDENT COMMITTED A CRIME, BUT
IT DOES NOT EXONERATE HIM.
IT'S CLEAR THAT RUDY GIULIANI
BELIEVES THE SECOND PART OF THAT
WAS SOMETHING THAT A SPECIAL
COUNSEL SHOULD NOT SAY BECAUSE
IF YOU CAN'T PROVE IT, YOU
SHOULDN'T SAY HE'S NOT
EXONERATED.
>> THE MAYOR SAID THAT WHEN THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL ROBERT MUELLER
COULDN A FINAL DECISION
ON THE WHOLE ISSUE OF
OBSTRUCTION HE WAS HANDING IT
OVER TO THE ATTORNEY GENERAL TO
MAKE THAT DECISION.
>> SO ONCE AGAIN, WE DON'T KNOW
THAT'S WHAT ROBERT MUELLER
INTENDED AT ALL UNTIL WE SEE
THAT UNDERLYING REPORT.
ROBERT MUELLER SAID, THIS DOES
NOT EXONERATE HIM.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE HE'S PRESENT
ING THE LEGAL ARGUMENTS ON BOTH
SIDES.
AND HE'S GOING TO LEAVE THAT FOR
CONGRESS TO DECIDE.
I THINK WHEN WE'RE SEEING IS THE
WHITE HOUSE STRATEGY THAT
BETWEEN THE BARR SUMMARY AND
MUELLER REPORT TO CAPITALIZE ON
THE CHAOS AND CONFUSION IS AND
THROW AS MUCH SAND AS POSSIBLE
IN HOPING A TO GET A NARRATIVE
THAT WILL STICK.
>> IT'S POSSIBLE ALSO THAT THERE
WAS SOME DISAGREEMENT AMONG THE
LAWYERS WORKING FOR MUELLER.
AND THAT THEY HAD A DIFFICULT
TIME CLEARLY, REACHING SOME KIND
OF DECISION.
HE DID PUNT IT.
NOW WHETHER HE EXPECTED BARR TO
MAKE THAT DECISION OR NOT
REMAINS TO BE SEEN.
>> WE'LL HAVE A LOT MORE ON THIS
COMING UP.
HAVE TO TAKE ANOTHER QUICK
BREAK.
OTHER IMPORTANT NEWS WE'RE ALSO
FOLLOWING IN A STUNNING TWIST, A
PROSECUTOR DROPS 16 FELONY
COUNTS AGAINST JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
I'LL TALK TO CHICAGO'S MAYOR
RAHM EMANUEL, HE'S STANDING BY
LIVE AND CALLING IT AWHITEWASH.
I'LL ALSO DISCUSS THEHING ■■■ WC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE KAMALA
HARRIS.
SHE'S HERE LIVE IN THE SITUATION
ROOM.
Hi.
Maria Ramirez!
Mom!
Maria!
Maria Ramirez...
McDonald's is committing
150 million dollars
in tuition assisnce,
education, and caree
advising programs...
Mom and Dad: Maria Ramirez!!!
to help mo employees
achieve their dreams.
Now, eyeliner goes NYC-proof.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil
Mom and Dad: Maria Ramirez!!!
from Maybelline New York.
Smudge resistant.
Sweat resistant.
Waterproof.
Up to 36-hour wear
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil.
Only from Maybelline New York.
They're America's
biopharmaceutical researchers.
Pursuing life-changing cures
in a country that fosters
innovation
Here, they find breakthroughs...
Like a way to fight cancer
by arming a patient's own
T-cells...
Because it's not just about
the next breakthrough...
It's all the ones after that.
(VO)
We're Carvana,
the company who invented
car vending machines
and buying a car
100% online.
Now we've created a brand new
way for you to sell your car.
Whether it's a few years old
or dinosaur old,
we want to buy your car.
So go to Carvana
and enter your license plate,
answer a few questions,
and our techno-wizardry
calculates your car's value
and gives you a real offer
in seconds.
When you're ready,
we'll come to you,
pay you on the spot,
and pick up your car. Thñ
So ditch the old way
of selling your car
and say hello
to the new way...
at Carvana.
You're turning onto the
street
when you barely
clip a passing car.
Minor accident
—no big deal, right?
Wrong. Your insurance
company is gonna raise
your rate after the other
car got a scratch so small
you coulda fixed
it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that
pen and use it to sign up
with a different
insurance company.
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because of
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪