isn't working for you,
ask your gastroenterologist
about ENTYVIO®.
ENTYVIO®.
Relief and Remission
within reach.
>>> HAPPENING NOW, BREAKING
NEWS.
DEMOCRATIC PLANS, HOUSE DEMPS
HOLD AN URGENT CONFERENCE CALL
TO DISCUSS IMPEACHING PRESIDENT
TRUMP AS THEY STRUGGLE TO LEVEL
AN EFFECTIVE RESPONSE TO THE
RELEASE OF THE REDACTED MUELLER
REPORT.
WHAT WILL THEIR NEXT STEPS BE?
>>> CALLING McGAHN.
THE HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE
CHAIRMAN SUBPOENAS FORMER WHITE
HOUSE COUNSEL DON McGAHN,
SEEKING DOCUMENTS AND TESTIMONY
FOR THE INVESTIGATION INTO
POSSIBLE OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE
BY PRESIDENT TRUMP.
WHAT DOES McGAHN KNOW ABOUT THE
PRESIDENT'S EFFORTS TO UNDERMINE
THE MUELLER INVESTIGATION?
>>> RESTRAINING CONGRESS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND HIS SON SUED
TO BLOCK HOUSE DEMPS FROM
GETTING HIS FINANCIAL RECORDS
AND ASKED A JUDGE TO SLAP A
RESTRAINING ORDER AGAINST
LAWMAKERS, BLOCKING THEIR
SUBPOENA.
WILL THE COURT SIDE WITH
CONGRESS OR THE PRESIDENT?
>>> AND AMERICANS KILLED, AT
LEAST FOUR U.S. CITIZENS
CONFIRMED TO BE AMONG THE ALMOST
300 PEOPLE KILLED IN THE EASTER
SUICIDE BOMBINGS TARGETING
CHURCHES AND LUXURY HOTELS IN
SRI LANKA.
TONIGHT, A KEY SUSPECT WITH
POSSIBLE TIES TO ISIS HAS
EMERGED.
>>> WE WANT TO WELCOME OUR
VIEWERS IN THE UNITED STATES AND
AROUND THE WORLD.
I'M WOLF BLITZER.
YOU'RE IN "THE SITUATION ROOM."■
>> Announcer: THIS IS CNN
BREAKING NEWS.
>> THE BREAKING NEWS THIS HOUR,
CNN HAS LEARNED THAT HOUSE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN
JERRY NADLER HAS SUBPOENAED
FORMER WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL DON
McGAHN, THE CLEAREST SIGN YET
THE PANEL IS PLANNING A DEEP
DIVE INTO POSSIBLE OBSTRUCTION
OF JUSTICE BY PRESIDENT TRUMP.
ALSO BREAKING, DEEPLY DIVIDED
HOUSE DEMPS HOLDING A
HIGH-STAKES CONFERENCE CALL
DISCUSSING WHETHER OR NOT TO
MOVE TO IMPEACH THE PRESIDENT
BASED ON THE FINDINGS OF SPECIAL
COUNSEL ROBERT MUELLER.
AND TONIGHT SOURCES ARE TELLING
CNN THE U.S. IS NARROWING IN ON
A KEY TERRORIST IT BELIEVES IT
TIED TO BOTH ISIS AND THE SRI
LANKA TERROR ATTACKS WHO KILLED
ALMOST 300 PEOPLE INCLUDING FOUR
AMERICANS.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT AND MORE
WITH CONGRESSMAN OF THE
INTELLIGENCE AND OVERSIGHT
COMMITTEES.
AND OUR CORRESPONDENTS AND
ANALYSTS ARE ALSO STANDING BY.
FIRST LET'S GO STRAIGHT TO
CAPITOL HILL, OUR SENIOR
CONGRESSIONAL CORRESPONDENT MANU
A RAJU IS JOINING US.
FIRST, WHAT ARE YOU FINDING OUT
ABOUT THE SUBPOENA FOR DON
McGAHN?
>> Reporter: THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE MAKING A MOVE TO
SUBPOENA DON McGAHN, THE FORMER
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL ASKING HE
TURNOVER RECORDS BY MAY 7.
ASKING HE APPEAR IN PUBLIC BY
MAY 21st, AND AN INDICATION OF
THIS PANEL'S AGGRESSIVE
INVESTIGATION INTO POTENTIAL
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
McGAHN A CENTRAL PLAYER IN THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION FOR THE
FIRST TWO YEARS, AN INDIVIDUAL
WHOSE NAME WAS MENTIONED
THROUGHOUT THE MUELLER REPORT,
AND WHO THE PRESIDENT ASKED TO
FIRE THE SPECIAL COUNSEL ROBERT
MUELLER, AND McGAHN APPARENTLY,
ACCORDING TO THE MUELLER REPORT,
RESISTED IN DOING SO.
NOW, THIS IS ALL PART OF THE
NEXT SERIES OF STEPS THAT DEMPS
WANT TO TAKE TO MOVE FORWARD.
THEY WANT TO MOVE FORWARD IN THE
OBSTRUCTION INVESTIGATION, LOOK
INTO POTENTIAL ABUSES OF POWER
IN THE WHITE HOUSE, AND EXPLORE
DEEPLY EVERYTHING THAT BOB
MUELLER UNCOVERED IN HIS
TWO-YEAR INVESTIGATION.
NOW, NEXT MONTH IS GOING TO BE A
KEY MONTH FOR THE HOUSE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE.
BILL BARR, THE ATTORNEY GENERAL,
EXPECTED TO COMMENT ON THE FIRST
COUPLE DAYS OF MAY.
THEN BOB MUELLER EXPECTED TO
ALSO COME IN.
NO DATE HAS BEEN SET YET FOR HIS
TESTIMONY.
AND NOW DON McGAHN, THE SUBPOENA
ISSUED FOR HIS APPEARANCE.
AND THIS IS NOT GOING TO BE THE
LAST ACTION TAKEN BY THIS
COMMITTEE.
FOUR OTHER FORMER WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIALS HAVE -- MAY SOON GET
THEIR SUBPOENAS.
THE PANEL HAS AUTHORIZED JERRY
NADLER TO GIVE THEM THE
SUBPOENAS.
HE HAS THOSE IN HIS BACK POCKET,
WOLF, BUT THIS IS ALL PART OF
WHAT DEMPS PLAN TO DO NOW THAT
THE MUELLER INVESTIGATION IS
OVER.
FIGHT FOR THE FULL UNREDACTED
MUELLER REPORT, POTENTIALLY GO
TO COURT OVER IT, AND■ñ■ BEGIN
WITNESS TESTIMONY, INCLUDING
PUBLIC TESTIMONY FROM THE FORMER
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL, DON McGAHN.
>> AMIDST THIS -- ■MANU,
DEMOCRATS HAVE BEEN A
KEY CONFERENCE CALL ABOUT A PATH
FORWARD ABOUT THE MUELLER
REPORT.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT?
>> Reporter: THE CALL IS
ONGOING.
IT STARTED AT 5:00.
THERE WAS SOME DISCUSSION ABOUT
THE ISSUE OF IMPEACHMENT.
ONE INDIVIDUAL WHO BROUGHT UP
IMPEACHMENT WAS MAXINE WATERS.
I'M TOLD THAT THE HOUSE
FINANCIAL SERVICES CHAIRMAN, THE
PERSON WHO HAS PUSHED FOR
IMPEACHMENT, CALLED FOR THE
PRESIDENT TO BE I MPEACHED.
MADE IT CLEAR TO HER COLLEAGUES
ON THIS CALL SHE'S NOT ASKING
MEMBERS TO GET BEHIND HER ON
THIS.
SHE SAID SHE IS PURSUING THIS
AND NOT ORGANIZING AN EFFORT
BEHIND IT.
THAT IS A RELIEF OF SOMEWHAT TO
DEMOCRATIC LEADERS TRYING TO
TAMP DOWN CALLS FOR IMPEACH THE.
ANOTHER INDIVIDUAL ADAM SCHIFF,
THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
CHAIRMAN, SAID ANY IMPEACHMENT
DISCUSSION NEEDS TO BE THOUGHT
ABOUT SOBERLY, ONLY IF THE
COUNTRY IS BEHIND IT.
NOT FOR THE BENEFIT OF DEMPS OR
ONE POLITICAL PARTY, JERRY
NADLER DID NOT TALK ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT, I AM TOLD, BUT LAID
OUT THE NEXT STEPS IN THE
INVESTIGATION.
ANNOUNCED DON McGAHN AS WELL.
THE COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN LAID OUT
ALSO VARIOUS STEPS THEY ARE
TAKING.
RICHARD NEAL, THE HOUSE WAYS AND
MEANS CHAIRMAN, INDICATED HE
STILL PLANS TO PURSUE THE
PRESIDENT'S TAX RETURNS.
A DEADLINE FOR THAT TOMORROW.
BUT HE SAID THAT HE WOULD
PROCEED CAUTIOUSLY IN TRYING TO
GET THOSE TAX RETURNS.
ELIJAH CUMMINGS, THE HOUSE
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN
WANTS TO FOCUS ON SECURITY
CLEARANCE PROBLEMS THAT
APPARENTLY OCCURRED AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
HE RATZED CONCERN ABOUT THE LACK
OF DOCUMENTS TURNED OVER TO THIS
COMMITTEE.
FROM WHAT I'M HEARING, WOLF, AT
THE MOMENT, THERE HASN'T BEEN
MUCH PUSH BACK ABOUT THE
IMPEACHMENT OR DESIRE BY THE
DEMOCRATIC LEADERS TO POUR COLD
WATER ON T. ONE CONGRESS MANAGE,
JARED HUFFMAN OF CALIFORNIA, DID
MAKE A COMMENT SAYING, LOOK, WE
NEED TO CONSIDER NOT JUST THE
CONSEQUENCE OF IMPEACHING THE
PRESIDENT, BUT ALSO WHAT THE
CONSEQUENCE WOULD BE OF NOT
IMPEACHING THIS PRESIDENT, AND
THAT'S ONE ARGUMENT THATx■■ADVO
HAVE BEEN SAYING.
WE HAVE TO USE A MAJORITY FOR
SOMETHING, POTENTIALLY GO DOWN
THE ROAD OF IMPEACHMENT.
BUT AT THE MOMENT DEMOCRATS FEEL
PRETTY GOOD THEIR CAUCUS IS IN
LINE WHICH IS TO INVESTIGATE
BEFORE DECID IMPEACH.
>> MANU RAJU UP ON CAPITOL HILL,
THANK■> BRI OUR CHIEF
CORRESPONDENT JIM ACCOSTA.
DON McGAHN IS A KEY PLAYER WITH
A LOT OF DIRECT÷÷xPRESIDENT TRU
UNDERMINE THE RUSSIA PREOBE.
WHAT ARE YOU HEARING?
>> THAT'S RIGHT, THE WHITE HOUSE
IS AWARE OF THE SUBPOENA COMING
FROM THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE.
THEY'RE NOT COMMENTING ON IT.
WE'RE NOT EXPECTING A COMMENT
ANY TIME SOON.
BUT IPOSE A COMMENT COULD BE
COMING SHORTLY FROM THE
PRESIDENT.
WE'LL HAVE TO WAIT AND SEE WHAT
HAPPENS.
ALSO WAIT AND SEE WHAT DON
McGAHN'S REPRESENTATION, WHAT
HIS ATTORNEY SAYS ABOUT ALL OF
THIS.
THAT COULD BE COMING SOON AS
WELL.
BUT PRESIDENT TRUMP IN THE
MEANTIME, WOLF, HE IS TRYING TO
CONVINCEHE PUBLIC TO BELIEVE
HIM AND NOT THE MUELLER REPORT.
THE PRESIDENT INSISTED TODAY
THAT HIS AIDES ALWAYS OBEY HIS
ORDERS DESPITE WHAT THE MUELLER
REPORT SAYS.
JUST TODAY I WAS TOLD BY A
FORMER ADMINISTRATION OFFICIAL
THAT THERE WERE WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIALS WHO INDEED DID DECLINE
TO CARRY OUT THE PRESIDENT'S
ORDERS.
AND THE PRESIDENT IS ALSO
CLAIMING HE'S NOT WORRIED ABOUT
BEING IMPEACHED, WHAT MANU RAJU
WAS TALKING ABOUT A FEW MOMENTS
AGO, EVEN THOUGH HE TALKED ABOUT
AND TWEETED ABOUT THIS PROSPECT.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
EVERYBODY.
HAPPY EASTER.
>>> AT THE WHITE HOUSE EASTER
ROLL, PRESIDENT TRUMP TOLD
CNN HIS ORDERS ARE ALWAYS
FOLLOWED.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED THAT YOUR
STAFF IS IGNORING YOUR ORDERS AS
THE MUELLER REPORT PORTRAYS?
>> NOBODY DISOWE BAZE MY ORDERS.
>> Reporter: BUT SPECIAL COUNSEL
ROBERT MUELLER'S REPORT SAYS
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
MUELLER REVEALED SOME TRUMP
AIDES AND ASSOCIATED DEFIED HIS
ORDERS EVEN THOSE AIMED AT
SHUTTING DOWN THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION.
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL RO WITH IN
HIS REPORT THE PRESIDENT'S
EFFORTS TO INFLUENCE THE
INVESTIGATION WERE MOSTLY
UNSUCCESSFUL.
THAT IS LARGELY BECAUSE THE
PERSONS WHO SURROUND THE
PRESIDENT DECLINED TO CARRY OUT
ORDERS.
DEMOCRATS WANT TO HEAR FROM DON
McGAHN AFTER IT WAS STATED IN
THE MUELLER REPORT HE REFUSED TO
FIRE THE SPECIAL COUNSEL.
WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS INSIST
THERE IS NOTHING WRONG WITH SUCH
AN ORDER.
>> IF THE PRESIDENT WANTED TO
FIRE BOB MUELLER, HE WOULD HAVE
THE IN OTHER WORDS, HE HAS THE
AUTHORITY TO DO THAT.
HE FIRED DIRECTOR COMEY.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT ALSO
APPEARS TO BE LAYING OUT THE
CASE AGAINST HIS OWN
IMPEACHMENT.
ONLY HIGH CRIMES AND
MISDEMEANORS CAN LEAD TO
IMPEACHMENTMENT THERE WERE NO
HIGH CRIMES BY ME, NO
OBSTRUCTION, NO COLLUSION, YOU
CAN'TEACH.IT WAS THE DEMOCRATS
COMMITTED THE CRIMES, NOT THE
QUESTION.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT, MR. PRESIDENT?
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT'S
OUTSIDE ATTORNEY IS RESPONDING
TO MUELLER'S FINDINGS ARGUING ON
CNN THAT IT WAS JUST FINE FOR
THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN TO ACCEPT
DIRT ON HILLARY CLINTON FROM
RUSSIA.
>> THERE IS NOTHING WRONG WITH
TAKING INFORMATION FROM
RUSSIANS.
>> THERE'S NOTHING WRONG --
>> DEPENDS ON WHERE IT CAME
FROM.
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS SAY
THAT'S UNACCEPTABLE.
>> I TOTALLY DISAGREE WITH
MR. GIULIANI.
THERE IS A LOT WRONG WITH TAKING
INFORMATION FROM AN ADVERSARY,
FOREIGN ADVERSARY FOREIGN
GOVERNMENT.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER MAJOR
DEVELOPMTHE
INVESTIGATION, THE TRUMP
ORGANIZATION IS NOW SUING HOUSE
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN
ELIJAH CUMMINGS TO BLOCK DEMPS
FROM OBTAINING THE PRESIDENT'S
FINANCIAL STATEMENTS FOR THE
LAST EIGHT YEARS, SAYING IN A
STATEMENT, IT'S UNUNPRECEDENTED
OVERREACH OF CONGRESSIONAL
AUTHORITY.
CUMMINGS FIRED BACK SAYING THE
PRESIDENT HAS A LONG HISTORY OF
TRYING TO USE BASELESS LAWSUITS
TO ATTACK HIS ADVERSARIES, BUT
THERE IS SIMILE MONTH VALID
BASIS TO FIGHT WITH THE DULY
AUTHORIZED SUBPOENA FROM
CONGRESS.
HERMAN KANE HAS DECIDED AGAINST
SEEKING A SPOT ON THE FEDERAL
RESERVE.
BUT THE PRESIDENT WAS HAVING
TROUBLE COMMUNICATING THE FACTS
ON THE TERRORIST ATTACKS IN SRI
LANKA.
AT ONE POINT TWEETING■p THAT 13.
MR. TRUMP ALSOED HE HAD
SPOKEN WITH THE PRESIDENT OF A
SRI LANKA.
TURNS OUT IT WAS THAT COUNTRY'S
PRIME MINISTER.
>>> AS FOR THE PRESIDENTS'S
ACTIONS LAID OUT IN THE MUE
REPORT, A FORMER ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIAL SAID MR. TRUMP COULD
HAVE USED MORE FIRM LEGAL
GUIDANCE EARLY ON IN HIS
PRESIDENCY.
WE SHOULD POINT OUT THE
PRESIDENT POSTED LATE IN THE DAY
IN THIS TWEET, ISN'T IT AMAZING
THE PEOPLE WHO WERE CLOSEST TO
ME BY FAR KNEW THE CAMPAIGN
BETTER THAN ANYONE WERE NEVER
MUELLER.LED TO TESTIFY BEFORE ■
IT IS UNCLEAR, WOLF, WHAT THE
T IS REFERRING TO THERE,
WHO HE'S REFERRING TO IN THIS
TWEET.
BUT TOP AIDES TO THE PRESID■■
WE'VE TALKED ABOUT THEM LIKE DON
cGAHN, BUT EVEN MR. TRUMP'S
SON-IN-LAW JARED KUSHNER, THEY
WERE ALL INTERVIEWED BY THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL.
SO THE PRESIDENT, IT■ SEEMS, IS
ONCE AGAIN TWIFSTING THE TRUTH O
UNDERMINE CONFIDENCE IN THE
MUELLER REPORT.
>> JIM ACCOSTA AT THE WHITE
HOUSE, THANK YOU.S GET MORE.
A MEMBER OF BOTH THE xxxxHE
OVERSI R COMMITTEE,
CONGRESSMAN, THANKS SO MUCH FOR
JOINING US.
I KNOW YOU JUST GOT OFF THIS
DEMOCRATIC CAUCUS CONFERENCE
CALL THAT YOU'VE BEEN ON FOR THE
PAST HOUR OR SO.
FIRST OF ALL, WHAT CAN YOU TELL
US, WHERE DOES YOUR PARTY STAND
RIGHT NOW ON THIS VERY SENSITIVE
ISSUE OF LAUNCHING PRELIMINARY
HEARINGS, FOR EXAMPLE, ON
IMPEACHMENT?
>> WELL, I THINK THAT CLEARLY
THERE'S DIFFERENCES OF VIEWS ON
THE ULTIMATE QUESTION OF
IMPEACHMENT RIGHT NOW.
BUT THERE IS A CONSENSUS ON ONE
THING, WHICH IS WE HAVE TO GET A
FULL UNREDACTED VERSION OF THE
MUELLER REPORT, AND THEN
SECONDLY, WE HAVE TO HAVE BOB
MUELLER AS WELL AS KEY WITNESSES
THAT ARE FEATURED IN THE REPORT
COME TESTIFY ON CAPITOL HILL.
>> WHERE DO YOU STAND,
CONGRESSMAN?
PART OF THE
PARTYOU WITH WHEN IT COMES
TO IMPEACHMENT?
>> I'M, I'M KIND OF IN THE CAMP
WHEREAS A FORMER PROSECUTOR IN
ILLINOIS, I BASICALLY LEARNED
THAT YOU HAVE TO INVESTIGATE
BEFORE YOU PROSECUTE.
AND RIGHT NOW I'M FOCUSED LIKE A
LASER ON, YOU KNOW, A THOUSAND
REDACTIONS IN THIS REPORT, AND
WHAT'S BEHIND THEM.
I'LL JUST GIVE YOU ONE EXAMPLE.
80% OF THE REDACTIONS ACTUALLY
COME IN VOLUME ONE OF THE REPORT
WHICH GOES TO THE POTENTIAL
CRIMINAL CONSPIRACY AND
INTERFERENCE BY THE RUSSIANS.
AND OF THE 14 MATTERS THAT HAVE
BEEN TRANSFERRED TO OTHER
JURISDICTIONS, 11 WERE
COMPLETELY BLACKED OUT IN THE
APPENDICES OF THE REPORT.
WE HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THE
WRONGDOING IS AT ISSUE IN THOSE
PROCEEDINGS.
NOR DO WE KNOW WHO THE TARGETS
ARE.
SO WE NEED TO UNDERSTAND THAT
ALONG WITH THE COUNTER
INTELLIGENCE FINDINGS TO HELP
PROTECT OUR DEMOCRACY AT THIS
POINT.
>> THEY MAKE THE ARGUMENT,
THOUGH, THAT THIS IS THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL BILL BARR, THAT
IF THEY WERE TO RELEASE THAT
INFORMATION T COULD UNDERMINE AN
ONGOING CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION,
LET'S SAY ABOUT THE PUT THE U.S.
ATTORNEY IN THE SOUTHERN
DISTRICT OF NEW YORK OR U.S.
ATTORNEY IN WASHINGTON, D.C.
>> WELL, TWO THINGS.
ONE, MEMBERS OF CONGRESS EVERY
DAY REVIEW CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION IN THE SKIFF, THE
UNDERGROUND BUNKER BENEATH THE
CAPITAL.
AND WE GET LARGE GROUP
CLASSIFIED BRIEFINGS.
SO THAT'S VERY IMPORTANT TO
KNOW.
THIS IS NO DIFFERENT.
AND THEN SECONDLY, YOU KNOW, WE
DON'T HAVE A KING.
WE HAVE A PRESIDENT, AND THE
PRESIDENT IS SUBJECT TO
OVERSIGHT BY THE PEOPLE.
AND WE ARE THE REPRESENTATIVES
OF THE PEOPLE AND WE SHOULD BE
ABLE TO CONDUCT OVERSIGHT.
IN ORDER TO DO SO, WE NEED THAT
INFORMATION.
>> JUST MOMENTS AGO, THE HOUSE
JUDICIARY CHAIRMAN JERRY NADLER
ISSUED A SUBPOENA FOR THE FORMER
E COUNSEL DON McGAHN
TO COME BEFORE THE COMMITTEE AND
TESTIFY.
HOW IMPORTANT WILL HIS TESTIMONY
BE AS DEMOCRATS WEIGH WHETHER TO
FORMALLY OPEN IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDINGS?
>> ASS KNOW IN THE REPORT,
MR. McGAHN TOLD THE PROSECUTORS
AND MR. MUELLER THAT HE WAS
ORDERED BY THE PRESIDENT SEVERAL
TIMES TO SHUTDOWN THE
INVESTIGATION OR FIRE BOB
MUELLER AND SO FORTH.
CONTRARY TO WHAT KELLYANNE
CONWAY SAID IN YOUR CLIP
PREVIOUSLY, THE PRESIDENT
ABSOLUTELY CAN COMMIT
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE IF HE HAS
A CORRUPT MOTIVE IN POTENTIALLY
FIRING BOB MUELLER.
AND SO BRINGING MR. McGAHN
BEFORE THE COMMITTEES OF
CONGRESS TO EXPLAIN WHAT HE
BELIEVES WERE THE MOTIVES AND
WHAT EXACTLY TRANSPIRED IS VERY
IMPORTANT IN KIND OF
ESTABLISHING WHETHER THERE WAS
OBSTRUCTION.
>> DO YOU BELIEVE, CONGRESSMAN,
SOME OF YOUR DEMOCRATIC
COLLEAGUES IN THE HOUSE BELIEVE
THAT THE LEADERSHIP MAY HAVE
GOTTEN AHEAD OF THEMSELVES BY
THROWING COLD WATER ON THE
PROSPECT OF IMPEACHMENT SO
QUICKLY OVER THESE PAST COUPLE
OR THREE WEEKS?
>> NO, I THINK THAT WHAT SPEAKER
PELOSI SAID TODAY WAS ABSOLUTELY
IMPORTANT, WHICH IS THAT WE HAVE
TO PUT TWO THINGS ABOVE
EVERYTHING, WHICH IS DUTY AND
OUR DEMOCRACY OVER ANY PARTISAN
MOTIVES.
I THINK CHAIRMAN SCHIFF ALSO
MADE IT VERY CLEAR THAT WHATEVER
WE DECIDE GOING FORWARD HASO
BE IN THE BEST INTEREST OF OUR
COUNTRY.
IT CAN'T BE ONE PARTY, IT CAN'T
BE FOR PARTISANANTAGE.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT WE WERE
ELECTED IN THE MAJORITY TO
UPHOLD, AND ALSO TO DELIVER ON
POCKETBOOK PRIORITIES, WHICH I
THINK IS ANOTHER IMPORTANT
FACTOR IN WHAT WE NEED TO DO
GOING FORWARD.
WE HAVE TO ADDRESS THE
POCKETBOOK ISSUES THAT THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE WANT US TO
ADDRESS, WHILE AT THE SAME TIME
SERVING AS A CHECK AND BALANCE
ON THE PRESIDENT.
>> BECAUSE SOME OF THE -- SOME
OF THOSE WANTING THE IMPEACHMENT
PROCESS TO BEGIN RIGHT AWAY
SAYING, IF YOU DON'T GO AHEAD
WITH IMPEACHMENT, THAT'S LALSO
POLITICAL DECISION BECAUSE
YOU'RE NOT LIVING UP TO THE
RESPONSIBILITIES OF THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES.
>> I UNDERSTAND WHERE THEY'RE
COMING FROM.
AND THAT'S OBVIOUSLY GOING TO BE
A FACTOR IN THE DECISION MAKING
GOING FORWARD.
I THINK ONE FACTOR THAT WE ALSO
HAVE TO CONSIDER IS THAT IN 18
MONTHS, THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ARE
GOING TO WEIGH IN ON WHAT THEY
THINK ABOUT THE MUELLER REPORT
AND WHETHER THEY BELIEVE
MR. TRUMP DESERVES A SECOND
TERM.
I THINK RIGHT NOW THE NEXT STEP
THAT I THINK EVERYBODY AGREES
ON, WOLF, WITHIN OUR CAUCUSES,
WE NEED TO CONTINUE THE
INVESTIGATION.
THERE ARE SOME VERY IMMEDIATE
NEXT STEPS BEFORE EACH OF THE
COMMITTEES.
YOU BROUGHT UP THE OVERSIGHT
COMMITTEE ON WHICH I ALSO SIT,
AND THERE WE DO NEED TO GET THE
ANSWERS TO OUR SUBPOENAS WITH
REGARD TO THE PRESIDENT'S
FINANCIAL RECORDS AS WELL AS THE
RECORDS WE HAVE REQUESTED FROM
DEUTSCHE BANK AND OTHER
FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONSITH
REGARD TO MR. TRUMP.
I THINK THAT ON THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE, WE HAVE TO GET AT THE
COUNTER INTELLIGENCE FINDINGS
THAT MR. MUELLER CAME ACROSS.
THERE MIGHT HAVE BEEN TIES
BETWEEN TRUMP OFFICIALS AND THE
RUSSIANS THAT MIGHT NOT BE
CRIMINALLY CONSPIRATORIAL IN
NATURE, BUT NONETHELESS, MIGHT
FORM THE BASIS OF KOMPROMAT,
THAT IS INFORMATION THAT THE
RUSSIANS CAN USE TO EXPLOIT OR
MANIPULATE TRUMP OFFICIALS OR
OTHERS IN OUR GOVERNMENT THAT
CAN ENDANGER OUR NATIONAL
SECURITY.
SO WE HAVE TO GET T
INFORMATION RIGHT AWAY.
>> THE PRESIDENT, HIS PERSONAL
LAWYERS ARE NOW SUING TO BLOCK A
SUBPOENA BY YOUR COMMITTEE, THE
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE, FOR HIS
FINANCIAL RECORDS FROM HIS
ACCOUNTANTS WHO DEALT WITH HIS
TRUMP ORGANIZATION OVER THE
YEARS.
WHY DO YOU THINK HE'S TRYING
THIS TACTIC FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN RESPONSE TO THIS SPECIFIC
SUBPOENA?
>> WELL, I THINK THAT THIS IS AN
AREA THAT'S OBVIOUSLY SENSITIVE
TO HIM, BUT IT'S SO CRUCIAL FOR
CONGRESS TO GET THESE RECORDS,
FOR TWO REASONS.
ONE, WE KNOW THAT UNDER OUR
BANKING STATUTES AND OTHER
STATUTES, YOU CANNOT COMMIT
FRAUD IN CONNECTION WITH
APPLICATIONS FOR LOANS AND OTHER
INSTRUMENTS IN CONNECTION WITH
FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONS.
AND SO THAT'S ONE REASON.
THE SECOND IS WE NEED TO
UNDERSTAND HIS ENTANGLEMENTS,
POTENTIALLY WITH OUR FOREIGN
ADVERSARIES.
AND SO WE NEED TO GET THOSE
FINANCIAL RECORDS.
I KNOW THAT CHAIRMAN NEAL ON THE
WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE IS ALSO
TRYING TO GET THE PRESIDENT'S
TAX RETURNS WHICH ALSO GET AT
THIS IMPORTANT QUESTION.
AND THEN OBVIOUSLY FROM THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE AND
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE AND OTHERS,
WE'RE TRYING TO GET THE
INFORMATION WITH REGARD TO
DEUTSCHE BANK AND POTENTIAL
MONEY LAUNDERING, WHICH IS ALSO
A SIGNIFICANT ISSUE THAT WE NEED
TO GET AT.
AGAIN, WE NEED TO PROTECT OUR
DEMOCRACIES RIGHT NOW.
WE NEED TO UNDERSTAND WHAT ARE
THE COUNTER INTELLIGENCE
IMPLICATIONS OF HAVING MR. TRUMP
POTENTIALLY HAVING TIES WITH THE
RUSSIANS.
>> BUT ARE YOU CONCERNED THAT
THIS WHOLE SUBPOENA BATTLE WOULD
GO ON AND ON -- COULD DRAG ON IN
THE COURTS FOR A LONG TIME?
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO ENFORCE
THESEUBPOENAS.
IT WOULD UNDERSCORE A WEAKNESS
OF CONGRESSIONAL SUBPOENAS.
>> I THINK THAT WE HAVE TO PRESS
FORWARD.
I BELIEVE THAT WE STAND ON FIRM
GROUND WITH REGARD TO THE
SUBPOENA POWER.
I THINK THAT THE PRESIDENT AND
HIS TEAM POTENTIALLY RISK
LITIGATING THESE SUBPOENAS
BECAUSE IF THEY WERE TO
VOLUNTARILY COOPERATE, THEY
COULD HELP TO POTENTIALLY KEEP
THE SCOPE MORE MANAGEABLE, AND
ESSENTIALLY DO THIS IN A
VOLUNTARY FASHION AND MAKE IT
EASIER ON THEM.
BUT IF THEY WANT TO GO THE
SUBPOENA ROUTE AND LITIGATE IT,
THAT'S UP TO THEM.
WE'L■HEM COURT.88
>> CONGRESSMAN, THANKS AS USUAL
FOR JOINING US.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THE BREAKING NEWS CONTINUES.
NEXT, NOW THAT FORMER WHITE
HOUSE COUNSEL DON McGAHN HAS
BEEN SUBPOENAED, WHAT WILL HE
REVEAL TO THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE ABOUT PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S ATTEMPTS TO UNDERMINE
THE MUELLER INVESTIGATION?
PLUS TRUMP CONTRADICTING THE
MUELLER REPORT INSISTING NOBODY,
NOBODY DISOBEYS HIS ORDERS
DESPITE A DOZEN ALLIES AND AIDES
WHO TESTIFIED UNDER OATH
OTHERWISE.
Did you eat all of your treats?
♪ Help! I need somebody
♪ Help! Not just anybody
♪ Help! You know I need someone
My insurance rates are probably
gonna double.
But dad, you've got
ALLSTATE.
WITH ACCIDENT FORGIVENESS
THEY GUARANTEE YOUR RATES
WON'T GO UP
JUST BECAUSE OF AN ACCIDENT.
Smart kid.
INDEED.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
[music playing]
(VO)
This is Jerry.
Jerry has a
membership to this gym,
but he's not using it.
And he has subscriptions to a
music service he doesn't listen
to and five streaming video
services he doesn't watch.
This is Jerry learning that
he's still paying for this stuff
he's not using.
He's seeing his recurring
payments in Control Tower
in the Wells Fargo Mobile app.
This is Jerry canceling
a few things. Booyah.
This is Jerry appreciating the
people who made this possible.
Oh look, there they are.
(Team Member)
This is Wells Fargo.
♪ ♪ ♪
THIS SIMPLE BANANA PEEL
REPRESENTS A BOLD IDEA:
A WAY TO CREATE ENERGY
FROM HOUSEHOLD TRASH.
IT NOT ONLY SAVES ABOUT
80% IN CARBON EMISSIONS...
IT HELPS REDUCE LANDFILL WASTE.
THAT'S WHY BP IS PARTNERING
WITH A CALIFORNIA COMPANY:
FULCRUM BIOENERGY.
TO TURN GARBAGE INTO JET FUEL.
BECAUSE WE CAN'T LET ANY
GOOD IDEAS GO TO WASTE.
AT BP, WE SEE
POSSIBILITIES EVERYWHERE.
TO HELP THE WORLD
KEEP ADVANCING.
(sobbing)
(speaking in foreign language)
I'm sorry I don't understand...
♪ Help! I need somebody
♪ Help! Not just anybody
♪ Help! You know I need someone
>>> WE'RE FOLLOWING THE BREAKING
NEWS.
HOUSE DEMOCRATS DISCUSSING
POSSIBLE IMPEACHMENT OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP IN A CONFERENCE
CALL.
LET'S DIG DEEPER WITH OUR
CORRESPONDENTS AND A
JACKIE, YOU'VE BEEN SPEAKING
WITH YOUR SOURCES ABOUT THIS
HOUR-LONG PLUS CONFERENCE CALL
THAT'S GOING ON.
WHAT ARE YOU HEARING?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THE CALL ACTUALLY JUST ENDED
MINUTES AGO, AND THE TAKE AWAY
HERE IS THAT NANCY PELOSI DID
NOT MAKE AN IMMEDIATE CALL TO
INITIATE IMPEACHMENT.
THERE WERE A FEW REALLY
ILLUMINATING QUOTES, THOUGH,
FROM THE SPEAKER WHERE SHE
BASICALLY TOLD HER CAUCUS THAT
EVEN A PROSECUTOR CAN PROSECUTE
A HAM SANDWICH OR NOT.
THAT'S PROSECUTORIAL DISCRETION.
BASICALLY SAYING SHE WANTS TO
COLLECT ALL THE FACTS BEFORE
COMING TO A CONCLUSION.
OTHER MEMBERS WENT ON TO RESPOND
THAT HER TACTICS HERE ARE REALLY
CAUTIOUS, BUT NEED TO BE DONE
EXPEDITIOUSLY.
THIS IS PRETTY TIME SENSITIVE.
MORE IMPORTANTLY, THERE WAS A
LOT OF CONVERSATION AND ASKS FOR
TALKING POINTS FROM
CONSTITUENTS.
RICHARD NEAL SAID HIS
CONSTITUENTS ARE REALLY
CONCERNED WITH TRUMP'S TAX
RETURNS, ASKED FOR TALKING
POINTS ON THAT.
THERE WERE ASKS FOR DATA AS IT
RELATES TO IMPEACHMENT AND ITS
EFFECT ON ELECTIONS.
THERE IS THIS CONUNDRUM HERE.
MEMBERS ARE SAYING, GUYS, WE
NEED TO TAKE THIS SLOW, IT IS A
POLITICAL PROCESS, AND WE KARNT
MOVE FORWARD WITHOUT A POLITICAL
SUPPORT HERE.
PELOSI CONTINUING TO SAY, HEY,
THIS CANNOT BE POLITICAL.
WE NEED ALL OF THE FACTS.
PELOSI ALSO SAID, WE HAVE TO
SAVE OUR DEMOCRACY WITHOUT
PASSION OR POLITICS, JUST THE
PRESENTATION OF THE FACTS.
THERE IS ALSO THIS RECOGNITION
HERE, WHILE IT WAS NOT
EXPLICITLY SAID BECAUSE, YOU
KNOW, AS MY SOURCES WERE SAYING,
THEY DIDN'T WANT TO COME OUT AS
POLITICAL OF PELOSI, THERE IS A
PROBLEM WITH NARRATIVES AND
MESSAGING.
THERE NEEDS TO BE MORE SALIENT
TALKING POINTS PUT OUT TO
MEMBERS SO THAT ALL OF THE
NARRATIVES DON'T COLLIDE HERE
ES AS THERE ARE
PROTRACTED LEGAL BATTLES.
>> LET ME GET REACTION TO THAT.
JEFFREY TUBIN, WHAT DO YOU
THINK?
>> IMPEACHMENT IS CERTAINLY NOT
HAPPENING.
IF ANYTHING -- NOTHING THAT
APPEARS IMMINENT IS GOING TO
CHANGE THAT.
HOWEVER, AS YOU SAW FROM THE
SUBPOENA TODAY TO DON McGAHN,
THE WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL WHO --
FORMER WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL, WHO
WAS FEATURED IN PERHAPS THE MOST
DRAMATIC MOMENT OF THE MUELLER
REPORT, THE DEMOCRATS ARE DOING
OVERSIGHT.
THEY ARE INVESTIGATING THE
OPERATIONS OF THE EXECUTIVE
BRANCH.
THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO
DO.
IT'S PERFECTLY POSSIBLE TO DO
THAT WHILE LEAVING THE QUESTION
OF IMPEACHMENT OPEN AND UNLIKELY
TO BE ADDRESSED, BUT THAT D
DOESN'T MEAN THE INVESTIGATION
SHOULD STOP.
>> THEY'RE MOVING WITH A
SUBPOENA TO GET DON McGAHN,
FORMER WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL,
DAVID SWERDLICK, TO GET HIM TO
TESTIFY.
>> DEMOCRATS HAVE ONE NOW, IF
THEY HAVE ONE AT ALL, THEY CAN
CALL ALL THESE WITNESSES TO
RE-TELL HER STORIES BEFORE THE
CAMERAS OR IN SOME CASES
PROBABLY BEHIND CLOSED DOORS,
THAT HAVE ALREADY BEEN LAID OUT
IN THAT REPORT.
DEMOCRATS CAN'T UNRING THE BELL
OF THE MARCH 24th LETTER FROM
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL.
THE WHITE HOUSE HAS THAT ONE IN
THEIR POCKET.
BUT THE WHITE HOUSE CAN'T UNRING
THE BELL OF THE FACT THAT THE
REPORT IS OUT THERE NOW, AND
THAT DEMOCRATS CAN GO ONE BY ONE
AND HAVE PEOPLE TELL THEIR
STORIES ALL OVER AGAIN TO THE
AMERICAN --
>> HOW WORRIED SHOULD WHITE
HOUSE OFFICIALS AND THE
PRESIDENT SPECIFICALLY BE IF DON
McGAHN ACTUALLY GOES BEFORE THE
CAMERAS, TESTIFIES BEFORE AN
OPEN SESSION OF THE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE?
>> WELL, THE STORIES HE TOLD TO
ROBERT MUELLER WERE PRETTY
DAMNING, AND THAT'S SOMETHING
THE PRESIDENT HAS SPENT THE LAST
SEVERAL DAYS FUMING ABOUT.
DON McGAHN IN PARTICULAR.
BECAUSE WHEN HE WAS IN THE WHITE
HOUSE, THE PRESIDENT AND HE HAD
THIS TROUBLED, AT TIMES
COMPLICATED RELATIONSHIP BECAUSE
THEY DIDN'T GET ALONG
PERSONALLY, OF COURSE, McGAHN
WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR HALF OF THE
JUDGES THAT HAS BEEN A BIG PART
OF THE PRESIDENT'S LEGACY.
THE QUESTION WHETHER HE'D GO ON
CAMERA AND TESTIFY TO THESE
EVENTS THAT HAPPENED TO HIM IS
SOMETHING THE WHITE HOUSE WOULD
CERTAINLY HAVE A LOT TO SAY
ABOUT BECAUSE SO FAR WHAT McGAHN
SAID, I BELIEVE HE WAS CITED
OVER 150 TIMES IN THE MUELLER
REPORT, REALLY IS REVEALING HOW
MUCH AT THE CENTER OF WHAT
DEMOCRATS WANT TO GET INTO, THE
CLAIMS, ALLEGATIONS OF
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE, HE'S
RIGHT AT THE CENTER OF THAT.
>> WHAT ARE THE DEMO)OPING
TO ACHIEVE BY GETTING DON McGAHN
BEFORE THE COMMITTEE?
BECAUSE HE SPOKE EXTENSIVELY, 30
HOURS, BEFORE MUELLER.
>> THAT IS A GREAT QUESTION.
I THINK THAT'S SOMETHING
DEMOCRATS ARE STILL FIGURING
OUT.
IT'S SOMETHING I KNOW WAS RAISED
ON THE CALL IN ADDITION TO
POTENTIALLY CALLING ATTORNEY
GENERAL BARR TO TESTIFY AS WELL,
BECAUSE I THINK A LOT OF
DEMOCRATS ARE CONCERNED THIS IS
GOING TO BE AN OPPORTUNITY TO
SORT OF CLEAN UP THEIR MESS AND
MAKE A GOOD SHOW FOR THE
PRESIDENT.
THAT BEING SAID, DON McGAHN DID
REVEAL SOME POTENTIALLY
PROBLEMATIC AND EMBARRASSING
INFORMATION ABOUT THE PRESIDENT,
AND THERE MIGHT BE MORE OF THAT
THAT EXTENDS BEYOND THE RED
LINES THER W C■FINED
TO.
>> GO AHEAD, JEFFREY.
>> JUST BECAUSE SOMEONE IS
MENTIONED IN A 450-PAGE
SINGLE-SPACED REPORT IS VERY
SEPARATE FROM SEEING SOMEONE
TELL A STORY TO A NATIONAL
AUDIENCE ON TELEVISION.
I MEAN, LOOK, WE ARE A NATION OF
VIDEO LEARNERS.
THE IDEA THAT THE PRESIDENT --
YOU KNOW, THE PRESIDENT TOLD DON
McGAHN TO FIRE ROBERT MUELLER,
AND THEN McGAHN WAS INSTRUCTED
TO LIE ABOUT THAT INSTRUCTION,
IT'S ONE THING TO REED THAT IN
PRINT.
IT'S ANOTHER THING TO HEAR IT.
AND I DON'T THINK THE DEMOCRATS
HAVE ANYTHING TO EXPLAIN AWAY
AND WHY THEY WOULD WANT THE
NATION TO SEE THAT.
THAT'S OVERSIGHT.
OU THINK, JEFFREY, THAT THE
DEMOCRATS -- THEIR SUBPOENA,
THEY WANT O T COMPLETE
UNREDACTED, UNREDACTED MUELLER
REPORT, ALL 460 PAGES WITHOUT
ANYTHING BLACKED OUT, BUT THEY
ALSO WANT ALL THEERLYING
EVIDENCE THAT WAS COLLECTED.
NOW, 30 HOURS OF TESTIMONY BY
DON McGAHN, THAT'S SEVERAL
HUNDRED PAGES OF TRANSCRIPTS.
THEY WANT ALL OF THAT AS WELL,
DON'T THEY?
>> THEY DO.
I THINK THAT'S A REAL LONG SHOT
THAT THEY'D GET THAT.
THE IRONY HERE IS THE
REPUBLICANS, WHEN THEY WERE IN
CHARGE OF THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES, THEY GOT ALL
SORTS OF INVESTIGATIVE MATERIAL
IN THE BENGHAZI INVESTIGATION,
IN THE INVESTIGATION OF THE FBI
AGENTS INVOLVED WITH THE
BEGINNINGS OF THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION.
BUT I THINK A COURT ORDER
DIRECTING THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
TO TURNOVER MELLER'S MATERIAL IS
REMOTE.
NOW, THEY HAVE A BETTER CHANCE
OF GETTING THE REPORT.
IN ANY EVENT, THE LEGAL FIGHT
WILL EATP A LOT OF MONTHS RDLES
ULTIMATELY
>> IT WIN, YNGE
WITH THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITE
WHITE HOUSE.
LET ME PLAY THE CLIP.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED THAT YOUR
STAFF IS IGNORING YOUR ORDERS AS
THE MUELLER REPORT PORTRAYS?
>> NOBODY DISOWE BAZE MY ORDERS.
>> HE LOOKED AT YOU DIRECTLY AND
SAID NOBODY DISOBEYS MY ORDERS.
>> THAT CAME AFTER A WEEKEND
WHERE THE PRESIDENT WAS IN PALM
BEACH FUMING BECAUSE ONE OF THE
PORTRAITS THAT EMERGED FROM THIS
REPORT WHEN IT CAME OUT IS THAT
NOT ONLY IS THE PRESIDENT
DISHONEST AT TIMES, BUT HE ALSO
HAS A STAFF THAT OFTEN■■■■■■■■■
THEM OR TRIES TO MANAGE THEM.
■OMETHING THE PRESIDENT
RESISTS.
HE DOES NOT LIKE THAT PORTRAYAL
OF HIM AND HE WAS FURIOUS ABOUT
THIS.
AS WE REPORTED OVER THE WEEKEND,
MY COLLEAGUE KEVIN AND I, THE
PRESIDENT WAS ALSO SEEKING
ASSURANCES FROM PEOPLE■■■■■#■#■#
PORTRAYED IN THE REPORT, NAMELY
DON■■■■■■■■■■ GEOFF SESSION TZ,
CO LEWANDOWSKI, OTHERS, ARE
PEOPLE WHO DON'T WORK IN THE
WHITE HOUSE OR HAVE LEFT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
HE WANTS TO MAKE SURE THE PEOPLE
THAT ARE STILL THERE ARE
FOLLOWING HIS ORDERS, TREATING
HIM LIKE THE PRESIDENT'S ORDERS
AND NOT LIKE SOME KIND OF
SUGGESTION.
>> HOLD ON A SECOND, JEFFREY.
IGNORED OR DISOBEYED THE HO■
PRESIDENT'S ORDERS -- YOU CAN
SE■ PICTURES■■■■■■■F■■
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■OU CAN SEE■
ALLMES.
MANY OF■ THEM, YOU■■■■■NOW, JAC
THEY WERE PRETTY IMPORTANT IN
PROTECTING THE PRESIDENT FROM
DOING SOMETHING HE WOULD H
REGRETTED DOWN THE ROAD.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
THE BIGGEST CASE -- BIGGEST TAKE
WAY AND WHY THE DEMPS WANT DON
McGAHN TO TESTIFY BEFORE THE
HOUSE PUBLICLY IS THIS ANECDOTE
AS IT RELATES TO McGAHN TELLING
SPECIAL COUNSEL MUELLER THAT THE
PRESIDENT ORDERED HIM TO FIRE
MUELLER FROM LEADING THE
INVESTIGATION.
AND THE PRESIDENT WAS VERY UPSET
WITH HIM WHEN HE REFUSED TO DO
SO, AND WAS PRESSURING HIM TO
ISSUE A RETRACTION TO "THE NEW
YORK TIMES."
McGAHN REFUSED TO DO SO.
THE PRESIDENT, IF WE KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT HIM, DESPITE HIS
CLAIMS THAT THIS INVESTIGATION
IS OVER, DOES NOT LIKE■
LY SLIGHTED.
>> JEFFREY, GO AHEAD.
>> YEAH, JUST DON McGAHN VERY
LIKELY SAVED PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
PRESIDENCY BY DISOBEYING HIS
ORDERS.
THAT'S THE IRONY OF THE
PRESIDENT'S IRE THERE, HIS ANGER
AT PEOPLE, McGAHN, EVEN ROB
PORTER, K.T. MacFARLANE.
ALL THESE PEOPLE TOOK TRUMP'S
CRAZY ORDERS AND STOPPED THEM IN
A WAY THAT MAY HAVE PREVENTED
HIM FROM BEING FORCED FROM
OFFICE.
>> IMPORTANT POINT INDEED.
EVERYBODY STICK AROUND.
MUCH MORE ON ALL THE BREAKING
NEWS RIGHT AFTER THIS.
has been excellent.
They really appreciate
the military family
and it really shows.
With ahat USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
It was funny because
when we would call
another insurance company,
hey would say
“Oh we can't beat USAA”
We're the Webber family.
We're the Tenney's
We're the Hayles,
and we're USAA members for life.
♪
Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
♪♪
♪
Be right back.
With moderate
to severe Crohn's disease,
I was there, just not
always where I needed to be.
Is she alright?
I hope so.
So I talked to my doctor
about HUMIRA.
I learned HUMIRA is for people
who still have symptoms
of Crohn's disease
after trying other medications.
And the majority
of people on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom relief
and many achieved remission
in as little as 4 weeks.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have
happened; as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Be there for you, and them.
Ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA,
remission is possible.
♪♪
Dad:
Oh, hey guys!
Mom (on speakerphone):
Hi!
Son (on speakerphone):
Dad, I two goals today!
VO: Getting to a
comfortable retirement
doesn't have to be an
uncomfortable thought.
See how Lincoln can help.
My gums are irritated.
I don't have to worry about
that, do I?
Harmful bacteria lurk just below
the gum line.
Crest Gum Detoxify,
voted Product of the Year.
It works below the gum line to
neutralize harmful plaque
bacteria
and help reverse early gum
damage.
Gum Detoxify, from Crest.
For a nasty cold, take DayQuil
Severe with Vicks VapoCOOL.
Whoa!
And vaporize it with an intense
rush of Vicks vapors.
Ahhhhhhhhhh!
DayQuil Severe with Vicks
VapoCOOL.
The Daytime, Coughing, Stuffy
head,
Vaporize your cold, medicine.
>>> WE'RE BACK WITH OUR
CORRESPONDENTS AND OUR ANALYSTS.
CAITLYN, THE PRESIDENT'S LAWYER,
ONAL LAWYER RUDY GIULIANI,
WAS ON WITH JAKE TAPPER
YESTERDAY HERE ON CNN, A■
HAD THIS EXCHANGE.
LET ME PLAY THIS CLIP.
>> THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH
TAKING INFORMATION FROM
RUSSIANS.
>> THERE'S NOTHING WRONG --
>> DEPENDING WHERE IT CAME FROM.
IT DEPENDS ON WHERE IT CAME
FROM.
>> YOU WOULD HAVE ACCEPTED
INFORMATION FROM RUSSIANS
AGAINST A CLIENT -- AGAINST A
CANDIDATE --
>> I PROBABLY WOULDN'T.
I WASN'T ASKED.
I WOULD HAVE ADVISED OUT OF
EXCESS OF CAUTION, DON'T DO I
>> DOES THE WHITE HOUSE THINK
IT'S OKAY TO ENGAGE IN THIS KIND
OF ACTIVITY, EVEN IF IT DOESN'T
MEET A CRIMINAL THRESHOLD, BUT
MAYBE MORALLY IMPROPER?
>> I THINK IT DEPENDS ON WHO YOU
ASK IN THE WHITE HOUSE.
A LOT OF SENIOR PEOPLE IN THE
WEST WING OR PEOPLE WHO HAVE
BEEN IN WASHINGTON FOR A WHILE,
WOULD SAY NO AND ACTUALLY DO NOT
LIKE WHEN RUDY GIULIANI GOES ON
TV AND MAKES COMMENTS LIKE THAT
BECAUSE THEY THINK IT WEAKENS
THEIR OTHER ARGUMENTS THEY'RE
TRYING TO MAKE ABOUT THE MUELLER
REPORT.
AND, OF COURSE, RUDY GIULIANI
SAYING THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH TAKING INFORMATION FROM THE
RUSSIANS RAISES THE QUESTION,
THEN WHY WHEN THE WHITE HOUSE
WAS FIRST CONFRONTED WHEN "THE
NEW YORK TIMES" WAS GOING TO
REPORT DON JUNIOR AND JARED
KUSHNER MET IN THE TOWER, THEY
GAVE MISLEADING INFORMATION
ABOUT WHAT THAT WAS ABOUT.
IF THEY THOUGHTOTHING WAS
WRONG, WHY DIDN'T THEY SAY IT.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> THIS IS A CLASSIC CASE.
IF ONE OF PRESIDENT OBAMA'S KIDS
HAD MET WITH A RUSSIAN LAWYER IN
TRUMP TOWER OR OBAMA TOWER
BEFORE A CAMPAIGN AND TAKEN
INFORMATION FROM RUSSIANS THAT
WAS DAMAGING TO HIS OPPONENT,
THERE IS NO WAY THAT MAYOR
GIULIANI OR ANY OTHER SENIOR
REPUBLICAN WOULD BE SAYING THAT
THIS IS OKAY AND IT'S ONLY A
CRIMINAL MATTER, IT'S NOT A
MORAL MATTER.
I THINK WE'RE IN A SITUATION
HERE WHERE DEMPS ARE THE PARTY
THAT IS HAVING TO EVALUATE THIS
ON THEIR OWN BECAUSE REPUBLICANS
ARE NOT BREAKING RANKS FROM THE
FACT THAT IF THE PRESIDENT IS
NOT TO THE LETTER OF THE LAW,
GUILTY OF A CRIME, WHICH THE
REPORTS SUGGESTS THAT HE'S NOT,
THEN THEY ARE GOING TO STICK
WITH HIM AND NOT CRITICIZE HIM.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> I JUST THINK THAT RUDY GOING
OUT AND SAYING THIS UNDERSCORES
THE WORST PARTS OF THIST
FOR THE PRESIDENT, WHICH IS THIS
OVERALL IDEA THAT THE RUSSIANS
WERE WILLING HELP THE
PRESIDENT'S CAMPAIGN AND THE
CAMPAIGN WAS WILLING TO TAKE
THAT HELP IN RETURN.
THIS DIDN'T ULTIMATELY AMOUNT TO
EVIDENCE OF CONSPIRACY, BUT THAT
DOES NOT MEAN THERE WEREN'T ACTS
OF CONSPIRACY.
AND RUDY GOING ON TV REALLY QQQ.
>> LET ME GET THE LEGAL
PERSPECTIVE FROM JEFFREY TOOBIN.
>> RUDY GIULIANI MAY BE RIGHT
IT'S ILLEGAL TO ACCEPT A THING
OF VALUE FROM A FOREIGN SOURCE.
IS INFORMATION A THING OF VALUE?
THAT'S A COMPLICATED QUESTION.
SIMPLY MEETING AND TALKING,
ESPECIALLY A MEETING THAT SEEMED
TO HAVE GONE NOWHERE LIKE THE
TRUMP TOWER MEETING, I DON'T
THINK THAT WAS A CAMPAIGN
FINANCE VIOLATION.
I DON'T THINK A THING OF VALUE
CHANGED HANDS.
HOWEVER, I MEAN, I THINK AS
EVERYONE IS POINTING OUT, IT'S A
VERY BAD IDEA.
IT'S MORALLY REPUGNANT.
IT'S CONTRARY TO THE VALUES OF
HOW WE WRUN OUR CAMPAIGNS.
BUT IS IT ILLEGAL TO ACCEPT
INFORMATION ALONE FROM A FOREIGN
SOURCE?
PROBABLY NOT.
>> BECAUSE MUELLER HIMSELF CONC
I'LL REED THE LAD THE LINE.
DAMAGING INFORMATION IS VALUABLE
ULTIMATELY DELIVERED IN THE
MEETING WAS NOT VALUABLE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
OPPOSITION RESEARCH IS A THING
OF VALUE.
CAMPAIGNS PAY GOOD MONEY FOR IT.
BUT THIS MEETING TURNED INTO
SUCH A FIASCO THAT NOTHING OF
VALUE WAS TURNED OVER.
I GUESS FORTUNATELY, AS IT TURNS
OUT, FOR EVERYONE AFFILIATED
WITH THE PRESIDENT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, AS A TECHNICAL
LEGAL MATTER, I THINK GIULIANI
WAS RIGHT IN WHAT HE SAID.
POLITICALLY, ETHICALLY, MORALLY,
IT'S A VERY DIFFERENT STORY.
>> AS A TECHNICAL LEGAL MATTER,
I DO THINK YOU CAN MAKE THE CASE
THAT THERE WAS AN ATTEMPT OR A
CONSPIRACY TO GET -- TO COMMIT
CAMPAIGN FINANCE VIOLATION.
THAT BEING SAID, WOLF, I THINK
THAT JEFFREY IS RIGHT, THAT IT'S
A CLOSE QUESTION.
YOU CAN FIND BOTH THAT THIS WAS
NOT A CRIME AND ALSO THAT SMALL
C COLLUSION HAPPENED.
THAT MEMORABERS OF THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN PLAYED FTSE FOOTSIE.
>> THERE WILL BE A LOT MORE ON
ALL OF THIS, THE CNN TOWN HALLS
BEGIN RIGHT AT 7:00 P.M.
EASTERN, BACK TO BACK, TOWN
HALLS WITH MAJOR DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES.
THAT'S COMING UP MOMENTS FROM
NOW.
WE'LL TAKE ANOTHER QUICK BREAK.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
-We bought a house
in a neighborhood
with a lot of other
young couples.
Then we noticed
something...strange.
Oh, could you, uh,
make me a burger?
-Poof -- you're a burger.
[ Laughter ]
-Everyone acts like
their parents.
-You have a tattoo.
-Yes.
-Fun. Do you not work?
-So, what kind of mower
you got, Seth?
-I don't know.
Some kid comes over.
We pay him to do it.
-But it's not all bad.
Someone even showed us
how we can save money
by bundling home and auto
with Progressive.
Progressive can't protect you
from becoming your parents.
But we can protect
your home and auto.
Wow, before I refinanced I paid
so much on my grad school loans.
Progressive can't protect you
from becoming your parents.
So insane!
Speaking of insane, have I not
taken a vacation in 4 years?
I should probably do that, and
get a new car.
How about a road trip?
Or Tokyo?
Well I've got to celebrate,
because now I'm going to be
debt-free even sooner.
And this is why I SoFi.
When you refinance your student
loans with SoFi, you can save
thousands.
A migraine hope...
from Aimovig.
To be there for the good...
and not so good.
For the mundane.
The awe-inspiring.
The heart-racing.
The heartbreaking.
That's what life is all about...
showing up.
Unless migraine steals your
chance to say...
"I am here."
We aim to change that.
That's why we created...
Aimovig.
A preventive treatment for
migraine in adults.
One dose.
Once a month.
Aimovig is proven to reduce the
number of monthly migraine days.
For some, that number can be cut
in half or more.
The most common side effects
are pain,
redness or swelling at the
injection site and constipation.
It doesn't matter
what each day brings.
So long as you can say...
"I am here."
Aim to be there more.
Talk to your doctor
about preventing migraine
with Aimovig.
I'M ALEX TREBEK,
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
AND LOOKING TO BUY LIFE
INSURANCE ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
-THE THREE P'S?
-WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE,
AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 65 AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH
FOR YOU TOO.
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE #1 MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN,
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE
IS GUARANTEED.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
>>> WE'RE ONLY MOMENTS AWAY FROM
A MAJOR CNN TOWN HALL EVENT.
FIVE PROMINENT PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES ON THE STAGE.
WE'LL SPEAK WITH OUR POLITICAL
DIRECTOR DAVID CHALIAN IN JUST A
MOMENT.
LIVE PICTURES COMING IN FROM NEW
HAMPSHIRE, BUT FIRST WE HAVE
MAJOR BREAKING NEWS IN THE
TERROR BOMBINGS THAT LEFT NEARLY
300 PEOPLE DEAD, INCLUDING AT
LEAST FOUR AMERICANS.
OUR SENIOR INTERNATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT SAM KILEY IS
JOINING US FROM COLOMBO IN SRI
LANKA.
SAM, THERE ARE IMPORTANT
DEVELOPMENTS UNFOLDING.
WHAT ARE WE LEARNING?
>> Reporter: WELL, CNN'S BARBARA
STARR, WOLF, SOURCES SAY
INTELLIGENCE BELIEVES THEY KNOW
WHO THE KING PEN BEHIND THE
ATTACKS S. THEY ARE WORKING WITH
SRI LANKANS TO FIND OUT THE
EXTENT OF HIS NETWORK, BUT THEY
HAVE NOT YET SAID ANYTHING OTHER
THAN HE HAS ISLAMIST
CONNECTIONS, PERHAPS INSPIRED BY
THE SO-CALLED ISLAMIC STATE.
THE EXTENT OF THE COLD BLOODED
RUTHLESSNESS OF THIS GROUP,
THOUGH, WOLF, KILLED 290 PEOPLE
OR MORE, IS REVEALED BY SOME CCT
FOOTAGE WE OBTAINED FROM THE
SAINT SEBASTIAN CHURCH.
TAKE A LOOK AT HOW RUTH
LIEUTEN■@SS
THIS BOMBER WAS.
TODAY VIDEO SHOWS WHAT CHURCH
OFFICIALS BELIEVE IS A BOMB IN
HIS BACK PACK.
PATS A TODDLER ON THE HEAD AS
HE CROSSES THE CHURCH COURTYARD.
THEY IDENTIFY HIM AS A SUSPECT
IN ONE OF THE BOMBINGS.
WITHOUT?8?8?8?8?8?8?8?8?8?8?8?8
■b■b■b■
THE NEXT FRAME■■Ñ■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
EXPLODING HIS BOMB, KILLING AT
LEAST 122 PEOPLE WHOERE
CELEBRATING EASTER MASS.
>> IT BLASTED IN SUCH A WAY,
THERE WERE CHILDREN, THERE WERE
WOMEN AND ALL CLOSE BY, AND ALL
WERE BLOWN OFF ALMOST.
SO WE HELD MORE THAN 100 PEOPLE
WHO WERE KILLED ON THE SPOT.
>> Reporter: THE SRI LANKAN
MILITARY SAYS THERE WERE SIX
SUICIDE BOMBERS THOUGHT TO HAVE
ATTACKED TWO OTHER■A CHUD
THREE FIVE-STAR HOTELS WITHIN
MINUTES OF ONE ANOTHER ALL
AROUND THE SAME TIME.
LOCAL AND U.S. INTELLIGENCE
OFFICIALS BELIEVE THAT THE
SLICKLY COORDINATED PLOT IS THE
WORK OF AN INTERNATIONALO
ISIS-INSPIREDR GROUP.
IT COULD STRIKE AGAINN  SOON.
S?  DRAG NET WAS THROWN
ACROSS THE ENTIRE COUNTRY WITH A
STATE OF EMERGENCY ANNOUNCED AS
THEY UNCOVERED MORE OF THE
MURDER RUST PLOT.■IN COLOMBO, A
PERFORMED A CONTROLLED EXPLOSION
NEAR SAINT ANTHONY'S CHURCH, ONE
OF THE SCENES OF THE ATTACK.
A 6 FOOT PYTHON WAS FOUND CLOSE
TO THE AIRPORT ALONG WITH■8■8■
>>> THE MEMO FROM THE DEPUTY
INSPECTOR GENERAL OF POLICEY÷Yu
RAISE SECURITY DUE TO A
POTENTIAL ATTACK.
THE GOVERNMENT SPOKESMAN CAN'T
HIDE THE TRUTH FROM THE FAMILIES
OF MORE THAN 500 INJURED AND
NEARLY 300 DEAD, ALL OF THEM
AMERICANS.
FAMILY AND OTHER INSTITUTIONS
ABOUT THE IN THIS INCIDENT.
>> Reporter: AFTER 30 YEARS OF
CIVIL WAR AND TEN YEARS OF PEACE
SRI LANKANS BELIEVED THEY PUT
SCENES LIKE THIS BEHINDM.
WHOEVERAS BEHIND THIS WAS
CLEARLY INTENT ONG
FRICTION BETWEEN DIFFERENT
COMMUNITIES AND PERHAPS CAUSING
THEM TO QUESTION THEIR FAITH.
NOW THE CLEANUPq■ BEGINS.
>> WE CAN BUILD UP OUR CHURCH
BUT WE CAN'T BUILD UP OUR LIVES.
>> WHAT A HORRENDOUS TERRORIST
ATTACK.
SAM, BE CAREFUL OVER THERE.
WE'LL STAY IN CLOSE TOUCH WITH
YOU.
>>> JUST AHEAD DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES ABOUT TO
TALK IMPEACHMENT AS WELL AS SOM.
WE'RE GOING TO PREVIEW TONIGHT'S
CNN TOWN HALLS.
and stay done through
every season.
BEHR SEMI-TRANSPARENT STAIN.
Find it exclusively
at The Home Depot.
>>> COMING UP RIGHT AT THE TOP
OF THE HOUR, THE FIRST OF FIVE
BACK-TO-BACK CNN PRESIDENTIAL
TOWN HALLS.
OUR CONGRESSIONAL CORRESPONDENT
PHIL MATTINGLY AND OUR POLITICAL
DIRECTOR DAVID CHALIAN THERE IN
ER, NEW HAMPSHIRE.
THE■OCRATIC PARTY APPEARS
PRETTY MUCH DIVIDED RIGHT NOW
OVER THE ISSUE IMPEACHMENT.
WILL THAT ISSUE■ ■@■■■
■■■■■■■■■■■ CO BE,OLF.
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■ IS THE■■■■■■■
DIVIDED UP ON■■■■■■■■■■■■■+■■■■L
FIELD WE'VE SEE ELIZABETH
WARREN AND JULIANO COME
OUT IN FAVOR OF IT.
WE KNOW ELIZABETH WARREN WILL BE
OUT ON THE STAGE TONIGHT.OULD I
>> YOUR AUDIENCE EXCITED.I
A LOT OF YOUNG PEOPLE IN
AUDIENCE.
SENATOR WARREN IS PUSHING
FORWARD, A LOT OF POLICY■
INVOLVING STUDENT DEBT, COLLEGE
TUITION.
WHAT HAVE YOU■■■■■■ED?
>> WELL-TIMED GIVEN ALL THE
STUDENTS IN THE AUDIENCE
TONIGHT.
SENATOR WARREN GOING TO SPEAK
SHORTLY IN THE TOWN HALL.
THIS IS ANOTHER SWEEPING POLICY
FROM SENATOR WARREN, WHAT SHE
STAKES HER CAMPAIGN TO FROM BE
O'ROURKES.
LED IN LARGE PART B SENATOR
BERNIE SANDERS BUT IT GOES
FURTHER THAN THAT AND
PARTICULARLY ON THE ISSUE OF
LOAN FORGIVENESS,DENT LOAN
DEBT FORGIVENESS.
ANY HOUSEHOLD MAKING LESS THAN O
$50,000 IN LOAN FORGIVENESS.
IN TOTAL THIS WOULD COVER ABOUT
75% OF THE $1.5 TRILLION STUDENT
LOAN DEBT OUTSTANDING, GRANT
PROGRAMS FOR MINORITY AND LOWER
INCOME STUDENTS.
YOU'■ REPEATEDLY
WHETHER ON HEALTH CARE, ON THE
ENVIRONMENT, NOW ON STUDENT
LOANS.
SENATOR WARREN IS TRYING TO
STAKE HER CLAIM TO THE BIGGEST
AND BOLDESTS.
THAT HASN'T NECESSARILY PLAYED
OUT IN TERMS OF HAVING AN
IMMEDIATE PAY BACK IN THE POLLS.
BUT IT'S VERY CLEAR HER CAMPAIGN
AND COMFORTABLE WITH THIS
POSITION, A POSITION SHE'S HELD
ON CAPITOL HILL AND■■ YOU'LL
HEAR ABOUT IN A COUPLE OF HOURS
WHEN SHE TAKES THE STAGE,■■■■■■
)■■
ATES A■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■0
WHEN BIDEN ANNOUNCES.
>>ON'T THINK W■■HOUGHT AT
THE BEGINNING OF THIS PROCESS
HE'D BE THE 20th PERSON TO GET
IN.
A FRONT-RUNNER CLEARLY IN THE
POLLS.
WE'LL SEE IF+ HE HAS THE■■■■■ P
HAVE AND HOW HE PERFORMS, YOU
KNOW, ON THE TRAIL WITH THE
MODERN DAY DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
IT'S NOT THE SAME DEMOCRATIC
ELECTORATE HE FACED IN '98 WHEN
HE RAN NOR IN 2008.
I THINK THAT'S SOMETHING WE'LL
WATCHSELY AS HE EMBARKS ON
THIS JOURNEY, BUT HE DOES ENTER
AS SORT OF A BIG DOG IN THIS
RACE AND I■■■■■ DO /BE
IN BEFORE THE WEEK IS OUT.
>> 5 OF THE 19, ALMOST 20 WILL
BE ON THAT STAGE TONIGHT BEHIND
YOU.
DAVID, WHAT DO THEYEE T
TO SORT OF HELP THEMSELVES JUMP
AHEAD?
>> WELL,■■■■ ■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■?
IT'S ONE THING TO COURT THEM,
BUT DO THEY SHOW UP?
WHAT WE SAW IN THE 2018
MID-TERMS IS THAT THEY DID AND
WERE REALLY A PART OF THE
COALITION THAT SENT THE
DEMOCRATS INTO THE MAJORITY IN
THE HOUSE.
SO I DO THINK THAT THIS
CONSTITUENCY IS SO CRITICAL FOR
EACH OF FIVEDATES BIG
PART OF THAT.
BUT I ALSO THINK THIS IS THE
FIRST TIME, WOLF, WE'RE SEEING
ON THE STAGE TIME BEFORE THE
SAME AUDIENCE THE ABILITY TO
COMPARE THESE CANDIDATES TO EACH
OTHER.
IT'S NOT A ONE OFF ????????? IS.
>> THIS IS MAJOR MOMENT.
FIVE KEY DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES ABOUT TO THIS■■■
STAGE.