FOR HOSTING THIS EVENT.
IT'S BEEN AN AMAZING NIGHT.
FIVE OF THE TOP PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES HAVE SHARING THE SAME
STAGE TONIGHT WITH YOUNG ADULTS
FOR STUDENTS WHO PLAN TO VOTE IN
THEIR STATE AND PRIMARY
CAUCUSES.
WE'VE ALREADY HEARD FROM
SENATORS AMY KLOBUCHAR,
ELIZABETH WARREN AND BERNIE
SANDERS.
RIGHT NOW IT'S TIME TO WELCOME
TO THIS STAGE SENATOR KAMALA
HARRIS OF CALIFORNIA.
>> HI, HI.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> HAVE A SEAT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WOW, THEY'RE HAPPY TO SEE
YOU.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU GUYS.
>> LET'S GET TO IT.
WE WANT YOU TO GET AS MUCH OUT
OF THE NEXT HOUR AS POSSIBLE.
LET'S START WITH WHAT'S
DOMINATING THE NEWS, THE FALLOUT
FROM THE MUELLER REPORT.
>> YES.
>> WE HAVE A QUESTION FROM C
CARCARLA
ALVARADO, A SENIOR FROM
MASSACHUSETTS.
>> GOOD EVENING, SENATOR HARRIS,
IN LIGHT OF MUELLER'S REPORT DO
YOU BELIEVE THE DEMOCRATS A
CONGRESS SHOULD RECONSIDER THEIR
POSITION ON IMPEACHMENT?
>> IT DEPENDS ON WHO YOU'RE
TALKING TO ON WHAT THEIR
POSITION IS, HERE'S WHAT I FEEL
ABOUT IT AND THANK YOU FOR THE
QUESTION, CARLA.
LOOK, FOR THOSE OF US WHO HAVE
BEEN FOLLOWING THE INVESTIGATION
AND HAVE SEEN ANY PART OF THAT
REPORT IT IS VERY CLEAR THAT
THERE IS A LOT OF GOOD EVIDENCE
POINTING TO OBSTRUCTION AND
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
AND I BELIEVE VERY STRONGLY,
FIRST OF ALL LET ME JUST BE VERY
CLEAR -- THE TABLE SET.
I BELIEVE THAT WE NEED TO GET
RID OF THIS PRESIDENT.
THAT'S WHY I'M RUNNING TO BECOME
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
THAT IS PART OF THE PREMISE,
OBVIOUSLY, OF MY PLAN.
BUT I THINK WE ARE VERY GOOD
REASON TO BELIEVE THAT THERE IS
AN INVESTIGATION THAT HAS BEEN
CONDUCTED WHICH HAS PRODUCED
EVIDENCE THAT TELLS US THAT THIS
PRESIDENT AND HIS ADMINISTRATION
ENGAGED IN OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE.
I BELIEVE CONGRESS SHOULD TAKE
THE STEPS TOWARDS IMPEACHMENT.
BUT I WANT TO SAY THIS, BECAUSE
IT DOESN'T END THERE.
I ALSO WANT TO SAY THIS.
I'M ALSO A REALIST.
AND WHEN I LOOK AT WHAT HAS BEEN
HAPPENING OVER THE TWO YEARS AND
SOME MONTHS I'VE BEEN IN THE
UNITED STATES SENATE I HAVE ALSO
WITNESSED FOLKS IN THE UNITED
STATES CONGRESS AND IN
PARTICULAR IN THE GOP WHO HAVE
BEEN PRESENTED WITH MANY REASONS
TO PUSH BACK AGAINST THIS
PRESIDENT AND THEY HAVE NOT.
AND WHEN WE LOOK AT THE
IMPEACHMENT PROCESS THERE WILL
BE WHAT HAPPENS IN THE HOUSE AND
AN INVESTIGATION THAT TAKES
PLACE.
I THINK WE CAN BE PRETTY SURE IT
LOOKS LIKE THAT IS VERY LIKELY
TO HAPPEN AND THEN IT'S GOING TO
GO OVER TO THE SENATE.
AND THE HOUSE NEEDS TO BE A VOTE
BY A MAJORITY, A SIMPLE MAJORITY
AND THEN IT'S GOING TO COME OVER
TO THE SENATE AND I'VE NOT SEEN
ANY EVIDENCE, SINCE I'VE BEEN IN
THE UNITED STATES SENATE, THAT
THE UNITED STATES SENATE AND THE
REPUBLICANS HOLD THE MAJORITY,
I'VE NOT SEEN ANY EVIDENCE TO
SUGGEST THAT THEY WILL WEIGH ON
THE FACTS INSTEAD OF ON PARTISAN
ADHERENCE TO BEING PROTECTIVE OF
THIS PRESIDENT AND THAT'S WHAT
CONCERNS ME AND WHAT WILL BE THE
EVENTUAL OUTCOME.
WE HAVE TO BE REALISTIC ABOUT
THE END RESULT BUT THAT DOESN'T
MEAN THE PROCESS SHOULD NOT TAKE
HOLD.
>> THANK YOU, SENATOR.
A LOT OF STUDENTS HERE AT THE
HARVARD INSTITUTE OF POLITICS,
THEY'RE CONCERNED ABOUT GUN
VIOLENCE AND HOW THAT AFFECTS
THEM AND THEIR FAMILY MEMBERS.
BEN.
>> THANK YOU, SENATOR, AS A
FUTURE EDUCATOR I AM REALLY
BOTHERED THAT PUBLIC SCHOOLS ARE
BEING TARGETS FOR MASS
SHOOTINGS.
TWO DAYS AGO WAS THE 20th
ANNIVERSARY OF THE COLUMBINE
MASSACRE, BUT TWO DECADES LATER
NO MAJOR GUN CONTROL LEGISLATION
HAS BEEN PASSED.
AS PRESIDENT WHO WILL YOU GO
ABOUT KEEPING OUR SCHOOLS SAFE
AND KEEPING GUNS OUT OF THE
HANDS OF THOSE WHO SHOULD NOT
HAVE THEM?
>> I'M SURE THERE ARE PLENTY OF
STUDENTS HERE, WHILE YOU WERE IN
HIGH SCHOOL, EVEN MIDDLE SCHOOL,
THAT YOU HAD TO PARTICIPATE IN A
DRILL, RIGHT, WHERE YOU WERE
CONVENED AND YOUR TEACHERS
TAUGHT YOU ABOUT HOW YOU NEED TO
GO AND RUN IN A CLOSET BECAUSE
THERE MAY BE A MASS SHOOTER
ROAMING THE HALLWAYS OF YOUR
SCHOOL.
AND IN OUR AMERICA THAT SHOULD
NEVER HAVE TO HAPPEN.
CONVERSATIONS TAKE PLACE EVERY
NIGHT, CONVERSATIONS TAKE PLACE
EVERY NIGHT BETWEEN STATUTES AND
THEIR PARENTS, WHY DO THESE
THINGS HAVE TO HAPPEN, WHY DO WE
HAVE TO HAVE A DRILL LIKE THAT
AND THE RESPONSE IS THERE ARE
PEOPLE IN WASHINGTON, D.C.,
SUPPOSED LEADERS WHO HAVE FAILED
TO HAVE THE COURAGE TO REJECT A
FALSE CHOICE WHICH YOU'RE EITHER
IN FAVOR OF SECOND AMENDMENT OR
YOU WANT TO TAKE PEOPLE'S GUNS
AWAY.
SUPPOSED LEADERS IN
WASHINGTON, D.C. TO HAVE FAILED
TO HAVE THE COURAGE TO
RECOGNIZE, YOU WANT TO GO
HUNTING, THAT'S FINE, BUT WE
NEED REASONABLE GUN SAFETY LAWS
IN THIS COUNTRY, STARTING WITH
UNIVERSAL BACKGROUND CHECKS AND
A RENEWAL OF THE ASSAULT WEAPON
BAN BUT THEY HAVE FAILED TO HAVE
THE COURAGE TO ACT.
BEN HERE IS MY RESPONSE TO YOU.
UPON BEING ELECTED I WILL GIVE
THE UNITED STATES CONGRESS 100
DAYS TO GET THEIR ACT TOGETHER
AND HAVE THE COURAGE TO PASS
REASONABLE GUN SAFETY LAWS.
AND IF THEY FAIL TO DO IT, THEN
I WILL TAKE EXECUTIVE ACTION.
AND SPECIFICALLY WHAT I WILL DO
IS PUT IN PLACE A REQUIREMENT
THAT FOR ANYONE WHO SELLS MORE
THAN FIVE GUNS A YEAR THEY ARE
REQUIRED TO DO BACKGROUND CHECKS
WHEN THEY SELL THOSE GUNS.
I WILL REQUIRE THAT FOR ANY GUN
DEALER THAT BREAKS THE LAW THE
ATF TAKE THEIR LICENSE.
AND BY THE WAY, ATF, ALCOHOL,
TOBACCO AND FIREARMS, THEY'VE
BEEN DOING A LOT OF "A" ANDT■IF"
WE NEED TO FIX THAT.
AND THEN -- ON THE THIRD PIECE,
BECAUSE NONE OF US HAVE BEEN
SLEEPING THE LAST TWO YEARS,
PART OF WHAT'S HAPPENED UNDER
THE CURRENT ADMINISTRATION IS
THEY TYKE FUGITIVES OFF THE LIST
OF PROHIBITED PEOPLE.
I PUT THEM BACK ON THE LIST,
MEANING THAT FUGITIVES FROM
JUSTICE SHOULD NOT BE ABLE TO
PURCHASE A HANDGUN OR ANY KIND
OF WEAPON.
SO THAT'S WHAT I'D DO.
>> WOULD THIS BE YOUR FIRST
EXECUTIVE ACTION AS PRESIDENT?
>> WELL, IT DEPENDS ON WHAT ELSE
HAPPENS.
AFTER 100 DAYS.
LET'S SEE WHAT HAPPENS IN THE
FIRST 100 DAYS.
>> ALL RIGHT, FAIR ENOUGH.
ANGELA IS A FRESHMAN STUDYING
INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS.
SHE IS FROM NEW HAMPSHIRE.
ANGELA?
>> GOOD EVENING, SENATOR, MY
QUESTION IS AS A COLLEGE STUDENT
WITH OVER $25,000 OF DEBT IN MY
FIRST YEAR ALONE WHAT WILL YOU
DO TO ALLEVIATE THE FINANCIAL
BURDENS OF THE STUDENT DEBT
CRISIS.
DO YOU SUPPORT INITIATIVES SUCH
AS FREE COLLEGE, LOAN PROTECTIVE
LEGISLATION, OR STUDENT
REPAYMENT PLANS?
>> YEAH, ANGELA.
KNOW, LISTEN, THE STUDENTS
IN NEW HAMPSHIRE ARE AMONG THE
TOP FIVE IN THE COUNTRY WITH
STUDENT LOAN DEBT.
AND IT IS ABSOLUTELY
UNCONSCIONABLE THAT WE HAVE
STUDENTS IN AMERICA WHO ARE IN
ABSOLUTE FEAR ABOUT THE DEBT
THAT THEY WILL OWE UPON
GRADUATION.
AND I HAVE MET AND KNOW SO MANY
STUDENTS WHO ARE MAKING
DECISIONS ABOUT THEIR CAREER
BASED ON THEIR FEAR THAT THEY
MAY NOT BE ABLE TO PAY THEIR
BILLS.
I KNOW SO MANY STUDENTS WHO HAVE
GRADUATED WHO ARE MAKING
DECISIONS ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT
TO HAVE A FAMILY BASED ON THE
BURDEN OF THEIR STUDENT LOAN
DEBT AND BEING CONCERNED ABOUT
WHETHER THEY'RE GOING TO
ACTUALLY BE ABLE TO GET THROUGH
THE MONTH.
WE CANNOT AFFORD TO HAVE A
SYSTEM LIKE THIS, ESPECIALLY FOR
YOUNG PEOPLE WHO HAVE MADE AN
INVESTMENT OF THEIR TIME AND
THEIR RESOURCES BECAUSE THEY
ACTUALLY WANT AN EDUCATION TO
LIVE A PRODUCTIVE LIFE AND
CONTRIBUTE TO OUR SOCIETY AND BE
LEADERS.
HERE'S WHAT I WOULD DO
SPECIFICALLY.
I DO SUPPORT DEBT FREE COLLEGE.
I ALSO BELIEVE THAT WHAT WE NEED
TO DO IS WE NEED TO ALLOW
STUDENTS TO REFINANCE YOUR
STUDENT LOAN DEBT AND IN
PARTICULAR I'M SUPPORTING AN
INITIATIVE THAT WOULD ALLOW YOU
TO REFINANCE YOUR STUDENT LOAN
DEBTING TO BE ON PAR WITH
FEDERAL LENDING AMOUNTS.
FOR EXAMPLE, IF YOU -- PROBABLY
NONE OF YOU HERE, BUT ANY OF
YOUR OLDER BROTHERS AND SISTERS
IF YOU TOOK OUT STUDENT LOANS
BETWEEN 2006 AND 2013, THE
INTEREST RATE WAS ABOUT 7%.
WHAT I AM PROPOSING IS
REGARDLESS OF THE INTEREST RATE
AT THE TIME THAT YOU TOOK OUT
OUR STUDENT LOANS, THAT UPON
REPAYMENT IT WOULD HAVE TO BE AT
3.5%.
THE OTHER THING IS THIS.
PART OF THE ISSUE IS THAT TERMS
OF REPAYMENT THERE IS NO
CONNECTION BETWEEN WHAT YOU OWE
AND YOUR INCOME.
WHAT I WOULD BE REQUIRING IS
THAT THERE BE A ROBUST PROCESS
BY WHICH INCOME-BASED REPAYMENT
WOULD BE THE NORM.
AND FINALLY LET'S LOOK AT THE
FACT THAT FOR ALL OF YOU AND ALL
OF ANYBODY WHO HAS APPLIED FOR
FINANCIAL AID THAT IS AN AWFUL
PROCESS.
YOU GUYS KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT.
ALL THOSE PAGES.
YOU CAN'T BARELY GET THROUGH
THAT FORM.
AND SO PART OF WHAT WE NEED TO
DO IS SIMPLIFY THAT PROCESS.
BUT WE HAVE GOT TO DO A BETTER
JOB IN THIS COUNTRY BECAUSE, YOU
KNOW, I LOOK AT SOMETHING LIKE,
FOR EXAMPLE, TEACHERS.
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN SPENDING A
LOT OF TIME, I THINK A LOT ABOUT
EDUCATION IN TERMS OF EVERY
ASPECT OF IT FROM STUDENT LOANS
TO WHAT WE NEED TO DO TO PAY OUR
TEACHERS THEIR VALUE.
AND  NUMBER OF TEACHERS WHO
HAVE LEFT THE PROFESSION OF
TEACHING BECAUSE THEY CAN'T
AFFORD TO PAY OFF THEIR STUDENT
LOANS RIGHT NOW WE'RE LOOKING AT
ACTUALLY A DEFICIT OF TEACHERS
BASED ON THE NUMBER OF STUDENTS
WE NEED TO ACTUALLY TEACH AND
THE FEW TEACHERS WE HAVE,
ESPECIALLY IN RURAL AREAS, IT'S
A BIG ISSUE AND CROSSES A LOT OF
SUBJECTS.
>> TEACHERS CAN'T PAY THEIR
LOANS.
ELIZABETH WARREN IS HERE, AS YOU
KNOW, SHE SAID THAT SHE SUPPORTS
STUDENT LOAN FORGIVENESS FOR 42
MILLION AMERICANS.
WOULD YOU GO THAT FAR?
DO YOU SUPPORT THAT?
>> WELL, I SUPPORT ANYTHING THAT
IS ABOUT REDUCING THE DEBT OF
STUDENT LOANS.
THAT'S AN IMPORTANT CONVERSATION
TO HAVE.
>> FAIR ENOUGH.
LET'S MOVE ON NOW.
RYAN WILSON IS HERE, A SOPHOMORE
AT HARVARD STUDYING NEUROSCIENCE
IN CALIFORNIA AND A SUPPORTER OF
JULIAN CASTRO.
RYAN.
>> HI, GOOD EVENING SENATOR
HARRIS, I'M A CONSTITUENT OF
YOURS FROM ORANGE COUNTY,
CALIFORNIA.
AT JANUARY TOWN HALL WHEN ASKED
ABOUT YOUR APPROACH TO UNIVERSAL
HEALTH CARE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGED
YOU WOULD SUPPORT -- HOW DO YOU
RESPOND TO THE 74% OF AMERICANS
WHO WISH TO HAVE THE OPTION TO
KEEP THEIR PRIVATE INSURERS?
>> WELL, I SUPPORT MEDICARE FOR
ALL.
AND I SUPPORT IT FOR A NUMBER OF
REASONS.
THAT INCLUDE THE FACT THAT THERE
ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE IN OUR
COUNTRY WHO SIMPLY DO NOT HAVE
ACCESS TO HEALTH CARE BECAUSE
THEY CANNOT AFFORD IT AND THAT'S
UNCONSCIONABLE AND I BELIEVE
IT'S A MORAL ISSUE AND IT IS A
SIGN OF WHETHER OR NOT WE ARE
GOING TO BE A CIVIL SOCIETY.
TO DETERMINE ARE PEOPLE GOING TO
HAVE ACCESS TO HEALTH CARE
SIMPLY BECAUSE THEY CAN AFFORD
IT WHEN, IN FACT, THAT SHOULD BE
A RIGHT AND NOT A PRIVILEGE OF
THE FEW WHO CAN AFFORD IT.
THAT IS THE VALUE WITH WHICH I
I WILL ALSO SAY THIS.ION.
ON THE ISSUE OF THIS WHOLE
DYNAMIC ABOUT ACCESS TO PRIVATE
INSURANCE, OF COURSE PRIVATE
INSURANCE YOU CAN GET
SUPPLEMENTAL INSURANCE AND ALL
OF THAT.
BUT LET'S NOT BE DUPED BY A
MESSAGING CAMPAIGN THAT HAS BEEN
WAGED FOR YEARS BY THE INSURANCE
COMPANIES TO HAVE YOU INTO
BELIEVING YOU NEED TO DEFEND
THEM.
YOU NEED TO DEFEND YOURSELF.
YOU KNOW WHAT, 91% OF THE
DOCTORS ARE IN MEDICARE.
SO THE IDEA AND THE SUGGESTION
THEY'RE TRYING TO MAKE TO YOU IS
REALLY A FALSE ONE.
YOU WILL BE ABLE TO HAVE YOUR
DOCTOR.
91% OF THEM ARE IN THE MEDICARE
SYSTEM.
AND I'LL TELL YOU ANOTHER THING,
AND IT'S A PERSONAL STORY, MY
MOTHER, WHO -- YOU KNOW, MY
MOTHER WAS ALL OF 5'0" TALL, IF
YOU WOULD HAVE MET HER, YOU
WOULD HAVE THOUGHT SHE WAS 7'0".
INCREDIBLE WOMAN, BREAST CANCER,
RESEARCHER.
WE GOT CANCER.
AND SHE ULTIMATELY PASSED AWAY
FROM CANCER.
BUT IF YOU HAVE EVER HAD THE
UNFORTUNATE EXPERIENCE OF GOING
THROUGH THE HEALTH CARE SYSTEM
WITH SOMEONE WHO HAS AN ACUTE
ILLNESS, I'M GOING TO TELL YOU
WHAT THAT IS.
IT IS HAVING A DOCTOR SAY TO YOU
HAVE YOU HEARD OF THE TERM
ANTICIPATORY GRIEF?
WHICH YOU HADN'T HEARD BEFORE
BUT WHEN YOU HEAR IT IT MAKES
PERFECT SENSE, YOU'RE STARTING
ALREADY TO GRIEVE THE LOSS OF
SOMEONE THAT IS STILL AROUND.
YOU HAVE THE EXPERIENCE OF GOING
IN AND OUT OF HOSPITALS HELPING
SOMEONE WHO IS FRAIL AND WEAK,
IN AND OUT OF CARS TO GET INTO A
HOSPITAL.
YOU LOOK AT MEDICAL CHARTS AND
SOMETIMES THE MEDICINE JIVES,
SOMETIMES IT DOESN'T, SOMETIMES
THE PEOPLE ARE PAYING ATTENTION
TO THIS IS THE MEDICATION THAT
CAUSES DROWSINESS THEY DON'T
WANT OR PAIN THEY CAN'T BEAR.
YOU GO THROUGH THE PROCESS OF
WORRYING ABOUT IS THERE
SOMETHING I CAN COOK AND BE ABLE
TO FOR YOU TO EAT AND HOLD DOWN.
THE PROCESS OF BEING CONCERNED
ABOUT CHEMOTHERAPY, CAN I GET
YOU SOMETHING SOFT ENOUGH TO
WEAR THAT WILL NOT IRRITATE YOUR
SKIN.
THANKFULLY OUR MOTHER HAD
MEDICARE, PEOPLE GOING THROUGH
THIS PROCESS EVERY DAY IN
AMERICA, FOR THEM TO ALSO HAVE
TO BE CONCERNED ABOUT HOW
THEY'RE GOING TO PAY THAT BILL
IS UNCONSCIONABLE.
AND THAT'S HOW I FEEL ABOUT THIS
SUBJECT.
COSTS SHOULD NOT BE THE BARRIER
TO RECEIVING THE CARE THAT WILL
RELIEVE YOU OF PAIN OR HELP
IMPROVE YOUR QUALITY OF LIFE.
AND WE'VE GOT TO GET THIS RIGHT.
THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
>> YEAH.
SO YOU MENTIONED THE INSURANCE
COMPANIES.
YOU DON'T FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE TO
DEFEND THE INSURANCE COMPANIES.
>> NO, I DON'T HAVE TO --
>> THE BILL THAT YOU
CO-SPONSORED WOULD EFFECTIVELY
ELIMINATE PRIVATE INSURANCE.
IS THERE ROOM FOR PRIVATE
INSURANCE IN --
>> OF COURSE THERE IS, FOR
SUPPLEMENTAL INSURANCE,
ABSOLUTELY.
>> FOR COMPANIES, FOR PRIVATE
INSURANCE COMPANIES.
>> LULT.
>> ROOM IN YOUR ADMINISTRATION
FOR THAT.
>> YEAH.
BUT LISTEN IN THIS BILL.
>> BUT DON, I THINK THAT IT'S
REALLY IMPORTANT TO TALK ABOUT
THE GOAL.
RIGHT, I MEAN, WE CAN TALK ABOUT
THE INTERMEDIATE STEPS.
BUT THE GOAL HAS TO BE, AND WE
ALL HAVE TO AGREE, ACCESS TO
HEALTH CARE IS A RIGHT AND
SHOULD BE THOUGHT OF AS A RIGHT
AND PUBLIC POLICY SHOULD CREATE
IT SUCH THAT IT IS A REAL RIGHT
AND NOT A PRIVILEGE FOR THOSE
WHO CAN AFFORD IT AND IT'S ONE
OF THE BIGGEST ISSUES IMPACTING
AMERICAN FAMILIES RIGHT NOW.
I'M TRAVELING THIS COUNTRY.
IT'S ONE OF THE BIGGEST ISSUES.
THE NUMBER OF PEOPLE WHO SIT
DOWN AND MAKE DECISIONS ABOUT
WHETHER THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE
ACCESS TO HEALTH CARE OR NOT
BASED ON MONEY, YOU WOULD BE
SHOCKED, ONE OUT OF FOUR
DIABETES PATIENTS IN OUR COUNTRY
CANNOT AFFORD THEIR INSULIN.
THERE IS A DRUG THAT HELPS SAVE
A LIFE IF THERE HAS BEEN AN
OVERDOSE OF OPIOIDS.
AND THAT DRUG CAN COST UP TO
$4,000.
THAT'S UNCONSCIONABLE.
>> LISTEN, BUT TO BE CLEAR, THIS
BILL THAT YOU CO-SPONSORED
ESSENTIALLY PHASES OUT PRIVATE
INSURANCE IN FOUR YEARS.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S RIGHT.
>> THAT'S WHAT THE STUDIES SHOW,
THAT IT WOULD PHASE OUT PRIVATE
INSURANCE.
>> I'M ACTUALLY SUPPORTING --
>> MEDICARE FOR ALL?
>> CO-SPONSORING WITH BERNIE
SANDERS PHASES OUT PRIVATE
INSURANCE COMPANIES --
>> AS THE MAIN SOURCE, BUT THERE
WILL STILL BE SUPPLEMENTAL,
THERE WILL STILL BE ACCESS TO
SUPPLEMENTAL INSURANCE.
MEDICARE FOR ALL UNDER THE CARE
I'M SUPPORTING WILL EXTEND
COVERAGE, IT DOES NOT COVER
DENTAL, VISION, HEARING AIDS,
UNDER THE PLAN MEDICARE FOR ALL
IT WILL COVER -- THOSE NEEDS
WILL BE COVERED.
THEY WILL BE AN EXTENSION OF IT,
INCLUDING MENTAL HEALTH
SERVICES, INCLUDING WHAT WE NEED
TO DO BETTER AROUND WOMEN HAVING
GREATER ACCESS TO REPRODUCTIVE
HEALTH CARE.
>> NOW THEEN NEW DEAL.
>> YES.
REEN NEW DEAL, EVERYONE
HERE WANTS TO KNOW ABOUT THAT.
MAX RATNER, NOW A STUDENT, HE
INTERNED FOR SENATOR ED MARKEY.
>> SENATOR HARRIS, THANK YOU FOR
TAKING MY QUESTION.
THE GREEN NEW DEAL IS NOT A LAW
BUT RATHER A MEMORANDUM THAT HAS
NO ACTUAL LEGISLATIVE EFFECT.
IT'S BEEN CHARACTERIZED AS
EXPENSIVE, DIVIDES DEMOCRATS AND
HAS NO CHANCE OF PASSING THROUGH
CONGRESS IN ITS CURRENT STATE.
WHY DO YOU SUPPORT IT?
>> I SUPPORT IT BECAUSE I, TO MY
CORE, KNOW THAT THE CLIMATE
CRISIS IS REPRESENTING AN
EXISTENTIAL THREAT TO WHO WE ARE
AS HUMAN BEINGS, WE HAVE
SUPPOSED LEADERS PUSHING SCIENCE
FICTION INSTEAD OF SCIENCE FACT
AND THIS IS TO OUR COLLECTIVE
PERIL IF WE DON'T TAKE THIS
MATTER SERIOUSLY WITH A SENSE OF
YOU ARE URGENCY.
THE GREEN NEW DEAL APPRECIATES
THAT WE NEED TO TAKE THIS
SERIOUSLY AND THE CLOCK IS
TICKING EVERY DAY ON THIS ISSUE
AND EVERY DAY WE FAIL TO ACT
WILL BE TO OUR COLLECTIVE
CONSEQUENCE.
THE U.N. HAS ALREADY SAID OVER
THE NEXT 12 YEARS IF WE DON'T
GET THIS STRAIGHT THERE WILL BE
SEVERE CONSEQUENCE AND THIS IS
WITHIN OUR ABILITY TO DO
SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
LISTEN, I HAVE -- FAMILIES ARE
IMPACTED BY THIS.
YOU KNOW, CHILDREN, SENIORS, WE
ALL NEED TO DRINK CLEAN AIR --
DRINK CLEAN WATER AND BREATHE
CLEAN AIR.
AND DON'T DRINK THE AIR.
YOU LOOK AT FARMERS.
FARMERS ARE IMPACTED BY THIS.
CLIMATE CHANGE.
YOU CAN LOOK AT THE FIREFIGHTERS
IN CALIFORNIA WHO ARE IMPACTED
BY CLIMATE CHANGE.
ACROSS THE BOARD PEOPLE ARE
BEING IMPACTED BY THIS.
LET'S ALSO LOOK AT THE FACT THAT
WE HAVE IN SO MANY STATES GREAT
WORK THAT IS HAPPENING THAT IS
ACTUALLY CONTRIBUTING TO THE
ECONOMY AROUND AN INVESTMENT IN
RENEWABLE ENERGIES.
THE BUREAU OF LABOR STATISTICS
CAME OUT WITH A LIST LAST YEAR
OF THE TOP 20 JOBS THAT ARE
GOING TO SEE THE GREATEST AMOUNT
OF GROWTH IN OUR COUNTRY OVER
THE NEXT TEN YEARS.
NUMBER ONE AND NUMBER TWO,
INSULATION MAINTENANCE OF WIND
TURBINES AND SOLAR PANELS,
LOOKING AT IT IN THE CONTEXT OF
WHAT WE KNEE TO BE TRUE ABOUT
WATER, WATER IS A PRECIOUS AND
DIMINISHING RESOURCE ON OUR
PLANET.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT WHAT'S
HAPPENING AROUND SHIFTING
POPULATIONS, AROUND THE GLOBE,
CLIMATE CHANGE IS ONE OF THE
MAIN FACTORS IN WHAT IS
HAPPENING.
THERE WAS A TIME AND STILL TO
THIS DAY WHERE WE'RE FIGHTING
WARS OVER OIL.
IN A SHORT MATTER OF TIME, GUYS,
WE'RE GOING FIGHTING WARS OVER
WATER.
PART OF WHAT WE CAN DO WITH THE
GREEN NEW DEAL IS HAVE A SENSE
OF URGENCY ON ALL THESE MATTERS,
INCLUDING THE PRECIOUS NATURE OF
WATER AND WHAT WE NEED TO DO TO
BE SMARTER ON PUBLIC POLICY.
I THINK, FOR EXAMPLE, THAT WE
NEED TO REALLY DIVERSIFY PUBLIC
POLICY ON WATER WITH AN EQUAL
EMPHASIS ON RECYCLING,
CONSERVATION, CAPTURE OF WATER,
STORAGE OF WATER.
DESALINATION.
WE NEED TO INVEST IN ELECTRIC
CARS.
WE NEED TO REDUCE GREENHOUSE GAS
EMISSIONS.
ALL OF THAT IS IN THE GREEN NEW
DEAL.
THE GREATEST THING ABOUT IT THAT
I AM REALLY ENJOYING, THIS IS
CAUSING THESE CONVERSATIONS TO
HAPPEN AROUND OUR COUNTRY IN A
WAY THEY'VE NOT BEEN IN THE LAST
FEW YEARS.
AND HOPEFULLY EVERYONE IS
UNDERSTANDING THAT SO MUCH OF
THE HARM WE ARE DOING TO OUR
PLANET IS CAUSED BY US AS HUMAN
BEINGS.
AND THE SOLUTIONS WILL BE
BECAUSE WE CHANGE OUR BEHAVIORS
WITHOUT MUCH REQUIREMENT OF
CHANGE TO LIFESTYLE AND IT WILL
BE URGENT IN TERMS OF THE WORK
WE NEED TO DO AND THE APPROACH
WE NEED TO HAVE.
BUT WE CAN SEE SUCCESS.
WE'VE SEEN IT IN CALIFORNIA.
IN CALIFORNIA WE MADE A DECISION
THAT WE WOULD GO BACK TO THE
1990 STANDARDS IN TERMS OF
EMISSIONS, BY THE YEAR 2020.
AND WE'VE ALREADY MET THOSE
GOALS.
THIS CAN HAPPEN.
WE CAN DO IT.
BUT THERE HAS TO BE LEADERSHIP
IN OUR COUNTRY.
AND THAT'S ONE OF THE MAIN
REASONS WE NEED A NEW PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO SPEAKING OF AIR AND WATER,
LET'S TAKE A BREATHER, GET A SIP
OF WATER AND WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK
WITH MORE OF CNN'S PRESIDENTIAL
TOWN HALL EVENT, STAY WITH US.
k.
Oh I love it. It's a great
razor.
It has that 'fence' in the
middle.
It gives a nice smooth shave.
Just stopping that irritation...
That burn that I get is really
life changing.
-Here comes the rain.
[ Horn honking ]
[ Engine revving ]
What's that, girl?
Flo needs help?!
[ Engine revving ]
Take me to her!
♪♪
Coming, Flo!
Why aren't we taking roads?!
Flo.
[ Horn honking ]
-Oh. You made it.
Do you have change for a dollar?
-This was the emergency?
[ Engine revving ]
Yes, I was busy!
-24-hour roadside assistance.
From America's number-one
motorcycle insurer.
-You know, I think
you're my best friend.
You don't have to say
I'm your best friend.
That's okay.
♪♪
Every day,
visionaries are creating
the future.
♪♪
So, every day,
we put our latest technology
and unrivaled network to work.
♪♪
The United States
Postal Service makes
more e-commerce
deliveries to homes
than anyone else
in the country.
♪♪
Because the future only
happens with people
who really know how
to deliver it.
Because the future only
happens with people
♪♪
Applebee's Bigger, Bolder
Grill Combos.
Now that's Eatin Good
in the Neighborhood.
The right gear...
matters.
Introducing the all-new
2019 Ford Ranger,
It's the right gear.
With a Terrain Management
System for... this.
A bash plate for... that.
An Electronic Locking Rear
Differential for...
Yeah... this.
Heading to the supermarket?
Get any truck.
Heading out here?
Get the Ford Ranger.
The only adventure gear
Built Ford Tough.
Great. Another wireless ad.
So many of them are full of this
complicated,
tricky language about their
network and offers
and blah blah blah blah blah
blah.
Look Sprint's gonna do things
differently,
and let you decide for yourself.
They're offering a new 100%
Total Satisfaction Guarantee.
Try it out and see the savings.
If you don't love it, get your
money back.
See? Simple.
Now Sprint's Unlimited Plan
comes with one of the newest
phones
included for just $35 a month.
So switch now.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO CNN'S
SPECIAL PRESIDENTIAL TOWN HALL
EVENT.
WE'RE IN MANCHESTER, NEW
HAMPSHIRE.
AND RIGHT NOW WE'RE TALKING WITH
CALIFORNIA SENATOR KAMALA
HARRIS.
IT'S GOOD TO HAVE YOU HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I'M GOING TO BRING IN VANESSA
CHAMBERS, A FRESHMAN STUDYING
COMPUTER SCIENCE.
FROM NEW ORLEANS.
>> I WAS JUST IN NEW ORLEANS,
ACTUALLY.
>> MY QUESTION TALKS ABOUT HOW
THIS COUNTRY PLANS TO ADMINISTER
REPARATIONS TO THE DESCENDANTS
OF FORMER SLAVES.
IT'S BEEN DISCUSSED HEAVILY.
GEORGETOWN JUST VOTED TO DEVOTE
A PORTION OF THEIR STUDENTS'
TUITION TO ADMINISTER
REPARATIONS TO THE DESCENDANTS
OF THE 272 SLAVES WHO WERE SOLD
IN THE 19th CENTURY TO SAVE THE
SCHOOL.
HOWEVER, THIS IS BUT A SMALL
STEP.
HOW -- WHAT ACTIONS, WHAT
SPECIFIC ACTIONS DO YOU PLAN TO
TAKE TO ADMINISTER REPARATIONS
FOR THIS UNPAID LABOR?
>> SO I'M ACTUALLY SUPPORTING A
BILL, THERE'S A CONGRESSWOMAN BY
A NAME OF SHEILA JACKSON-LEE
THAT'S WRITTEN THIS BILL OUT OF
THE HOUSE TO STUDY EXACTLY THE
RESPONSE TO YOUR QUESTION AND TO
YOUR POINT AND TO SUPPORT YOUR
POINT, LOOK, WE HAD CENTURIES OF
SLAVERY IN THIS COUNTRY.
WE HAD DECADES OF JIM CROW.
WE HAD LEGALIZED DISCRIMINATION
AND SEGREGATION.
AND THEN WE HAD DE FACTO
DISCRIMINATION AND SEGREGATION.
AND TO BELIEVE OR SUGGEST THAT
THOSE YEARS OF TREATMENT AND
ABUSE AND VIOLENCE AND CRIMES
DID NOT HAVE AN IMPACT IS TO
OVERLOOK THE FACTS OF HISTORY.
AND FOR THAT REASON I SUPPORT
THE LEGISLATION.
AND WHAT WE NEED TO DO TO THINK
ABOUT SPECIFICALLY WHAT IT MEANS
IN TERMS OF THE NEXT STEPS.
BUT I THANK YOU FOR THAT
QUESTION.
>> SENATOR, YES OR NO, DO YOU
SUPPORT FINANCIAL REPARATIONS?
>> I SUPPORT WE STUDY THAT.
LET'S LOOK AT THIS, FOR EXAMPLE.
ONE OF THE ISSUES THAT IS VERY
CLEAR IS THAT TRAUMA, YEARS OF
TRAUMA OR EVEN ONE EXPERIENCE
WITH TRAUMA CAN LEAD TO LIFELONG
CONSEQUENCES.
I'M SUPPORTING SOME WORK,
PARTISAN WORK THAT STARTED YEARS
AGO OF LOOKING AT CHILDREN WHO
ARE GROWING UP IN A COMMUNITY
WHERE THERE IS VIOLENCE AND IF
YOU LOOK AT THE ASSOCIATED THEN
PHYSICAL HEALTH EFFECTS
ASSOCIATED WITH EXPOSURE TO
TRAUMA AND WHAT THAT CAN MEAN IN
TERMS OF PHYSICAL DISABILITY,
NOT TO MENTION WHAT IT MEANS IN
A CHILD'S ABILITY TO LEARN AND
BE EDUCATED THERE ARE REAL
SSOCIATED WITH TRAUMA.
WHEN YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT THE■■
EXPERIENCED BECAUSE OF SLAVERY,
BECAUSE OF JIM CROW AND ALL
WE'VE SEEN IN TERMS OF
INSTITUTIONAL AND LEGAL
DISCRIMIATION AND RACISM, THIS
IS VERY REAL AND IT NEEDS TO BE
STUDIED AND WE NEED TO LOOK AT
HOW EXACTLY THE RESPONSE SHOULD
BE PLAYED OUT AND HOW IT SHOULD
WORK.
>> I DON'T NEED TO TELL YOU THAT
A BIG VOTING BLOC IN THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY, BLACK
AMERICANS, WHAT'S YOUR AGENDA
FOR BLACK AMERICA?
>> A NUMBER OF THINGS, FIRST OF
ALL, WE NEED TO DEAL WITH THE
ECONOMIC STATUS OF
AFRICAN-AMERICANS IN THIS
COUNTRY WHEN YOU LOOK AT IT IN
TERMS OF EVERYTHING FROM HOME
OWNERSHIP TO WAGES.
WE CAN SEE HUGE DISPARITIES.
AND SO THAT NEEDS TO BE
ADDRESSED.
LET'S LOOK AT AN ISSUE LIKE
MAT
MATERNAL MORTALITY.
I AM PRESENTING WHAT I BELIEVE
SHOULD BE THE RESPONSE TO THAT.
I HAVE STUDIED THIS ISSUE.
BLACK WOMEN ARE THREE TO FOUR
TIMES MORE LIKELY TO DIE IN
CONNECTION WITH CHILDBIRTH.
WHEN YOU STUDY THE ISSUE IT
BECOMES CLEAR IT IS REGARDLESS
OF THE SOCIO ECONOMIC STATUS, IT
WAS A MATTER OF RACIAL BIAS IN
THE HEALTH CARE DELIVERY SYSTEM.
THOSE WOMEN ARE NOT TAKEN AS
SERIOUSLY WHEN THEY SHOW UP AT
THE CLINIC OR THE DOCTOR'S
OFFICE OR THE HOSPITAL.
I'M LOOKING AT IT IN TERMS OF
BEING A PROUD MEMBER AND
GRADUATE OF AN HBCU, HOWARD
COMPUTER, WHAT WE NEED TO DO TO
SUPPORT OUR HBCUs.
I HAD A PIECE OF LEGISLATION
THAT'S ACTUALLY BEEN PASSED TO
INVEST FEDERAL RESOURCES IN PPO
RECOGNIZING THAT HBCUs PRODUCE
IN SOME PROFESSIONS THE MAJORITY
OF AFRICAN-AMERICANS THIS THOSE
PROFESSIONS.
THERE ARE A NUMBER OF ISSUES,
INCLUDING WHAT WE NEED TO REFORM
THE CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM.
>> THIS IS A FASCINATING
QUESTION THAT YOU'LL FIND,
COMING FROM DIANA DING, A JUNIOR
AT HARVARD, STUDYING COMPUTER
SCIENCE FROM SAN FRANCISCO.
>> HI, SENATOR, THANK YOU FOR
TABING MY QUESTION.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU HAVE SUPPORTED LEGALIZING
SEX WORK, HOW WILL YOU ENSURE
SEX WORKERS ARE DOING THIS WORK
BECAUSE THEY WANT TO AND NOT
BECAUSE THEY HAVE NO OPPORTUNITY
TO DO OTHER WORK GIVEN THAT SEX
WORKERS OFTEN COME FROM
MARGINALIZED COMMUNITIES.
>> WHAT I DON'T SUPPORT IS
CRIMINALIZING THESE WOMEN.
MY BACKGROUND, AS YOU KNOW, I
WAS A PROSECUTOR.
WHEN I WAS DISTRICT ATTORNEY OF
SAN FRANCISCO I INSTITUTED A
NUMBER OF POLICIES THAT WERE
FOCUSED ON WOMEN AND CHILDREN
AND HOW THEY WERE TREATED
FRANKLY WITH BIAS IN THE
CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM WHERE
THEY WERE CRIMINALIZED WITHOUT
REALLY LOOKING AT THE REAL
OFFENDER AND SO OFTEN THAT CASE
WAS THE PIMPS AND JOHNS, SO
WOMEN WERE ARRESTED AS BEING
PROSTITUTES.
I CREATED POLICIES SAYING WE
NEED TO FOCUS ON THE OTHER FOLKS
AND NOT JUST ON THE WOMEN.
I WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR AN
INITIATIVE IN SAN FRANCISCO THAT
WAS ABOUT RECOGNIZING THAT GIRLS
WHO ARE BEING TRAFFICKED WERE■]
PRS.■■■■■■■@
WHEN, IN FACT, T THE
VICTIMS OF AN INCREDIBLE AMOUNT
OF ABUSE AND HAD BEEN
TRAFFICKED.
AND SO I CREATED A WHOLE POLICY
IN SAN FRANCISCO THAT WAS, ONE,
INTENDED TO STOP CALLING THEM
TEENAGE PROSTITUTES, BUT INSTEAD
TO CALL THEM SEXUALLY EXPLOITED
YOUTH.
AND BECAUSE OF THE WORK THAT WE
DID WE THEN CREATED A SAFE HOUSE
FOR THESE YOUNG WOMEN SO THAT
INSTEAD OF THEM BEING ARRESTED
AND PUT IN JUVENILE HALL THEY
WOULD BE IN A SAFE HOUSE AND
THEN WE WERE RESPONSIBLE FOR
ACTUALLY GETTING LEGISLATION
PASSED THAT SAID THAT WHEN THOSE
JOHNS AND PIMPS ARE PROSECUTED
THEY SHOULD BE PROSECUTED IN
CONNECTION WITH THE SALE OF A
CHILD, AGAIN LOOKING AT WHAT WE
NEED TO DO TO FIGURE OUT WHO'S
DOING WHAT.
AS IT RELATES TO WOMEN WHO ARE
BEING TRAFFICKED I WAS ONE OF
THE LEADERS IN THE COUNTRY WITH
MANY OTHERS IN SAYING THAT BACK
PAGE NEEDED TO BE PUT OUT OF
BUSINESS BECAUSE THEY WERE IN
THE BUSINESS OF BASICALLY
ALLOWING THE TRAFFICKING, IN
PARTICULAR OF UNDERAGE GIRLS.
SO THIS IS SOMETHING I HAVE HAD
A LIFELONG EXPERIENCE WITH.
INCLUDING WHAT WE NEED TO GO
AFTER THOSE WHO TRAFFIC GIRLS
AND WOMEN AND BOYS.
WE SHOULD ALSO BE CLEAR ABOUT
THAT.
AND I TAKE IT VERY SERIOUSLY.
BUT WE SHOULD NOT BE
CRIMINALIZING WOMEN WHO ARE
ENGAGED IN CONSENSUAL, YOU KNOW,
OPPORTUNITIES FOR EMPLOYMENT.
BUT WE SHOULD DEFINITELY BE
CAREFUL AND BE SURE THAT THEY
ARE NOT BEING TRAFFICKED OR
ABUSED IN ANY WAY.
>> OUR NEXT QUESTION, SENATOR,
COMES FROM MARGARET McSHERRY, A
JUNIOR STUDYING POLITICS,
ORIGINALLY FROM MASSACHUSETTS,
MARGARET.
>> HELLO, SENATOR, A QUESTION
FOR YOU.
AS TENSIONS GROW BETWEEN THE
UNITED STATES IN NATIONS LIKE
RUSSIA AND NORTH KOREA WHAT
SHOULD BE DONE TO PREPARE THE
NATION POSSIBILITY OF
CYBERWARFARE?
>> THAT'S A GREAT QUESTION, I'M
SO GLAD YOU ASKED IT.
IT'S REALLY -- IT'S BEEN
CHALLENGING.
I'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT IT IN
THE UNITED STATES SENATE.
I SERVE ON THE SENATE HOMELAND
SECURITY COMMITTEE.
I SERVE ON THE SENATE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE.
YOU KNOW, NEWS FLASH, RUSSIA
INTERFERED IN THE ELECTION OF
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES.
AND, IN FACT, ON THAT POINT
ABOUT CYBERSECURITY, ONE, IT IS
REAL.
WHEN WE TALK ABOUT NATIONAL
SECURITY, TO YOUR POINT, A NEW
FORM OF WAR, WE SHOULD
UNDERSTAND, WILL BE CYBERATTACKS
AND CYBERATTACKS CAN TAKE A
NUMBER OF FORMS BUT USUALLY TO
OUR CRITICAL INFRASTRUCTURE.
WE'VE ALREADY SEEN ONE.
YOU KNOW WHAT, UNDER THE
PREVIOUS ADMINISTRATION OUR
ELECTION SYSTEM WAS DESIGNATED
AS CRITICAL INFRASTRUCTURE,
RIGHT?
SO WE ALREADY KNOW THAT WE HAVE
BEEN ATTACKED IN TERMS OF OUR
ELECTIONS.
WE SHOULD ALSO UNDERSTAND THAT
WE ARE VULNERABLE IN TERMS OF
OUR ELECTRICAL GRIDS.
ALL OF THE SYSTEMS THAT HOLD
TOGETHER OUR FINANCIAL SYSTEMS,
THAT HOLD TOGETHER OUR MEDICAL
CARE SYSTEMS.
AND WE HAVE GOT TO PAY GREATER
ATTENTION.
I HAVE A BILL THAT IS A
BIPARTISAN BILL THAT IS DESIGNED
TO STRENGTHEN STATES ELECTION
SYSTEMS FROM -- TO PREVENT THE
NEXT ATTACK.
IT'S A BIPARTISAN BILL.
AND THE LEADER IN THE UNITED
STATES SENATE WILL NOT PUT IT ON
THE FLOOR FOR A VOTE.
AND THIS WILL BE TO OUR
COLLECTIVE PERIL WHEN PEOPLE
PLAY POLITICS WITH AN ISSUE
THAT'S TRULY ABOUT OUR
VULNERABILITY AS A COUNTRY.
I WORKED ON THIS ISSUE WHEN I
WAS ATTORNEY GENERAL.
I WAS ATTORNEY GENERAL OF
CALIFORNIA FOR TWO TERMS AND A
LOT OF WORK WE DID THERE WAS
ABOUT MAKING SURE THAT WE WERE
FOCUSED ON THE VULNERABILITIES
THAT WE HAVE BECAUSE OF
TECHNOLOGY.
AND DOING WHAT WE CAN TO PROTECT
IT.
AS THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES I WILL TELL YOU THAT WILL
BE ONE OF MY NUMBER ONE ISSUES
BECAUSE AS FAR AS I THINK ABOUT
IT, YOU KNOW, WE'RE USED TO, AND
WE PREPARE FOR WAR BECAUSE WE
SHOULD AND WE SHOULD MAKE SURE
THAT WE'RE READY IN THE EVENT
OF -- WELL, THIS WILL BE A WAR
WITHOUT BLOOD.
AND WE ARE NOT PREPARED.
AND WE MUST BE.
BUT WE CANNOT BE IN DENIAL AND
THIS PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES IS IN UTTER DENIAL ABOUT
THE REALITIES.
>> FROM THE VULNERABILITIES OF
OUR CYBERSYSTEM TO THE
VULNERABILITIES NOW OF CHILDREN,
SOMETHING I KNOW THAT'S
IMPORTANT TO YOU.
I WANT TO BRING IN NICOLE
CINDERS, A STUDENT AT HARVARD, A
MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIEG.
>> YOU RECENTLY MENTIONED YOU
WERE GRANTED THE TRUANCY LAW.
ARE THERE ANY OTHER LAWS OR
POLICIES THAT YOU REGRET AS A
PROSECUTOR AND WHAT ACTIONS, IF
ANY, WOULD YOU TAKE TO REMEDY
THIS AS PRESIDENT?
>> LET ME BE CLEAR.
I ABSOLUTELY BELIEVE THAT
CHILDREN HAVE AND SHOULD BE
THOUGHT OF TO HAVE A
CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHT TO AN
EDUCATION, PERIOD.
SO THE TRUANCY INITIATIVE THAT
YOU'RE REFERRING TO WAS STARTED
BY ME WHEN I WAS DA BECAUSE I
TOOK A LOOK AT WHO THE HOMICIDE
VICTIMS WERE WHO WERE UNDER THE
AGE OF 25.
PEOPLE WERE USED TO THESE YOUNG
MEN BEING KILLED.
AND I SAID WAIT A MINUTE,
INSTEAD OF JUST RESPONDING WHEN
THEY ARE KILLED WITH PUTTING
MORE POLICE ON THE STREETS OR
HAVING GANG ENFORCEMENT
STRATEGIES, WHY AREN'T WE ASKING
THE QUESTION OF WHO ARE THEY?
I ASKED THAT QUESTION.
WHO ARE THESE YOUNG MEN UNDER ■
BEING KILLED?
AND I QUICKLY LEARNED THAT 94%
OF THEM WERE HIGH SCHOOL
DROPOUTS.
I THEN LOOKED CLOSER INTO THE
ISSUE AND LEARNED OF THE
CHRONICALLY AND HABITUALLY
TRUANT STUDENTS UP TO 40% OF
THEM WERE ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
STUDENTS, MISSING 50, 60, UP TO
80 DAYS OF AN 180 DAY SCHOOL
YEAR.
I DECIDED TO TAKE THE ISSUE ON.
AND I TOOK THE ISSUE ON FOR A
NUMBER OF REASONS.
ONE, UNDERSTANDING IN AN
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL TRUANT IS
THREE TO FOUR TIMES MORE LIKELY
TO BE A HIGH SCHOOL DROPOUT.
70% OF THE PRISONERS IN THE
UNITED STATES ARE HIGH SCHOOL
DROPOUTS.
AN AFRICAN-AMERICAN MAN A HIGH
SCHOOL DROPOUT, IS TWO-THIRDS
LIKELY TO BE IN JAIL OR DEAD.
I TOOK THE ISSUE ON, WHAT WE'VE
GOT TO DO IS PAY ATTENTION TO
THE FACT THAT THESE CHILDREN
AREN'T IN SCHOOL AND PUT ALL THE
RESOURCES NECESSARY TO GET THEM
IN SCHOOL.
AND GIVE THEIR PARENTS THE
RESOURCES, HOLD THE SCHOOL
DISTRICTS ACCOUNTABLE, WHY
AREN'T THE SCHOOL DISTRICTS
RAISING THE ALARM AND PUTTING
ALL THE RESOURCES POSSIBLE INTO
GETTING THESE KIDS TO SCHOOL
EVERY DAY?
AND AS A RESULT OF OUR
INITIATIVE, FIRST OF ALL, NOBODY
WENT TO JAIL.
AND AS A RESULT OF OUR
INITIATIVE WE IMPROVED
ATTENDANCE BY OVER 30%.
AND TO PUT A FINE POINT ON THIS,
WHEN WE LOOK AT THE ISSUE OF
EDUCATION AND OUR CHILDREN NO
CHILD SHOULD BE OVERLOOKED.
AND THIS IS WHAT THE SYSTEM
DOES, GUYS, FOR CERTAIN KIDS THE
SYSTEM REALLY DOESN'T EXPECT
MUCH FROM THEM.
THAT IS A HARSH REALITY IN MANY
PLACES.
AND SO WHEN THEY'RE NOT SHOWING
UP IN SCHOOL THE SYSTEM IS
JUST -- KEEPS MOVING.
AND I SAID THIS IS WRONG.
LET'S PUT A SPOTLIGHT ON THIS
ISSUE.
AND LET'S DEAL WITH IT BECAUSE
THESE CHILDREN HAVE A CAPACITY
EQUAL TO ANY CHILD IN ANY OTHER
SCHOOL DISTRICT.
AND YOU CAN BEST BELIEVE THE
COMMUNITY WHERE I WAS TALKING
ABOUT, A LARGE PART OF THOSE
COMMUNITIES HAD AN ANNUAL
INCOME, HOUSEHOLD INCOME OF
$15,000.
YOU THINK OF THE CHILDREN IN
THOSE SCHOOL DISTRICTS THAT HAD
AN ANNUAL INCOME OF 150 OR
$300,000.
YOU THINK THE ALARMS WOULD NOT
HAVE BEEN RAISED IF THOSE
CHILDREN HADN'T BEEN ATTENDING
SCHOOL EVERY DAY, MUCH LESS
MISSING UP TO 80 DAYS OF 180 DAY
SCHOOL YEAR?
THAT'S WHY I TOOK THAT ISSUE ON.
>> ANOTHER ISSUE THAT I WANT TO
TALK TO YOU ABOUT, THIS IS
REALLY IMPORTANT, I'M NOT SURE
IF YOU WERE WATCHING EARLIER,
BUT SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS SAID
THAT HE IS IN FAVOR OF FELONS
BEING ABLE TO VOTE WHILE SERVING
IN PRISON.
HE WAS ASKED SPECIFICALLY ABOUT
PEOPLE LIKE THE BOSTON MARATHON
BOMBER, ALSO PEOPLE WHO ARE
CONVICTED OF SEXUAL ASSAULT.
AND HE SAID, THIS IS A QUOTE,
THE RIGHT TO VOTE IS INHERENT TO
OUR DEMOCRACY, YES, EVEN FOR
TERRIBLE PEOPLE.
DO YOU AGREE WITH THAT, SENATOR?
>> I AGREE THAT THE RIGHT TO
VOTE IS ONE OF THE VERY
IMPORTANT COMPONENTS OF
CITIZENSHIP.
AND IT IS SOMETHING THAT PEOPLE
SHOULD NOT BE STRIPPED OF
NEEDLESSLY, WHICH IS WHY I HAVE
BEEN A LONG ADVOCATE OF MAKING
PEOPLE INFORMALLY INCARCERATED
ARE NOT DENIED THE RIGHT TO
VOTE.
IN SOME STATES THEY'RE
PERMANENTLY DEPRIVED OF THE
RIGHT TO VOTE.
POLICIES THAT GO BACK TO JIM
CROW, POLICIES THAT GO BACK TO
THE HEART OF POLICIES THAT HAVE
BEEN ABOUT DISENFRANCHISEMENT,
POLICIES THAT CONTINUE TODAY AND
WE NEED TO TAKE IT SERIOUSLY.
>> PEOPLE WHO ARE IN --
CONVICTED, IN PRISON, LIKE THE
BOSTON MARATHON BOMBER, ON DEATH
ROW, PEOPLE WHO ARE CONVICTED OF
SEXUAL ASSAULT, THEY SHOULD BE
ABLE TO VOTE?
>> I THINK WE SHOULD HAVE THAT
CONVERSATION.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE MORE WITH
SENATOR KAMALA HARRIS, THIS TOWN
HALL EVENT RIGHT HERE AFTER THIS
BREAK.
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
Yes. In fact,d
these right here.
Oh, I thought you guys
just did shipping.
No we do printing,
packing, faxing,
notarizing, shredding,
mailboxing,
copying, taping, binding,
Uh huh...
consulting, designing,
returning,
storing, and freighting.
Oh, and of course, shipping.
So you're into shipping?
We also do printing,
packing, faxing...
Come in to The UPS Store today
for every ING your small
business needs.
And of course, shipping.
>> TECH: At Safelite AutoGlass,
we really pride ourselves
on making it easy
to get your windshield fixed.
>> TEACHER: Let's turn in your
science papers.
>> TECH VO: This teacher always
puts her students first.
>> STUDENT: I did mine
on volcanoes.
>> TEACHER: You did?! Oh, I
can't wait to read it.
>> TECH VO: So when she had
auto glass damage...
she chose Safelite.
With Safelite, she could see
exactly when we'd be there.
>> TEACHER: You must be Pascal.
>> TECH: Yes ma'am.
>> TECH VO: Saving her time...
[HONK, HONK]
>> KIDS: Bye!
>> TECH VO: ...so she can save
the science project.
>> KIDS: Whoa!
>> KIDS VO: ♪ Safelite repair,
Safelite replace ♪
Uh-oh, looks like someone's
still nervous about buying
a new house.
Is it that obvious?
Yes it is.
You know, maybe you'd worry less
if you got GEICO to help with
your homeowners insurance.
I didn't know GEICO could helps
with homeowners insurance.
Yep,
they've been doing it for years.
What are you doing?
Big Steve?
Thanks, man.
There he is.
Get to know GEICO and see
how much you could save on
homeowners and
renters insurance.
>>> WELCOME BACK HERE LIVE IN
NEW HAMPSHIRE FOR A CNN SPECIAL
DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL TOWN
HALL, AND WE WANT TO THANK
SENATOR KAMALA HARRIS FOR BEING
HERE.
LET'S JUMP INTO THE QUESTIONS.
BRING IN SAHIL, A SOPHOMORE AT
HARVARD.
HE'S SUPPORTING SENATOR BERNIE
SANDERS.
>> HI, SENATOR.
>> HI, SAHIL.
>> AS A FELLOW MIXED PERSON OF
AFRICAN AND INDIAN DESCENT, HOW
DOES OUR IDENTITY SERVE YOU AS
PRESIDENT OF THIS COUNTRY?
>> THAT'S A GREAT QUESTION.
WELL, YOU KNOW, THERE IS
SOMETHING THAT I FEEL VERY
STRONGLY ABOUT THIS MOMENT IN
TIME.
I THINK OF THIS AS BEING AN
INFLECTION POINT IN THE HISTORY
OF OUR COUNTRY.
I THINK THIS IS A MOMENT IN TIME
FOR A VARIETY OF REASONS THAT IS
REQUIRING ULL TO LOOK IN THE
MIRROR, EACH ONE OF US AND
COLLECTIVELY TO LOOK IN A MIRROR
AND ASK A QUESTION.
THAT QUESTION BEING WHO ARE WE?
AND I BELIEVE PART OF THE ANSWER
TO THAT QUESTION IS WE ARE
BETTER THAN THIS.
THE OTHER PART OF IT IS
UNDERSTANDING THAT IN THIS
INFLECTION MOMENT THERE ARE VERY
POWERFUL VOICES IN OUR COUNTRY
RIGHT NOW THAT ARE TRYING TO SOW
HATE AND DIVISION AMONG US.
AND WE NEED TO SPEAK MANY
TRUTHS.
THE VAST MAJORITY OF US HAVE SO
MUCH MORE IN COMMON THAN WHAT
SEPARATES US AND I KNOW THAT TO
BE TRUE.
I KNOW IT TO BE TRUE BECAUSE
I'VE BEEN EXPOSED TO MANY
CULTURES, RIGHT, YOU GOT ME.
RIGHT.
THERE YOU GO.
SO I KNOW IT TO BE TRUE.
I KNOW IT TO BE TRUE BASED ON
WHAT I CALL THE MINUTE OF THE
NIGHT THOUGHT.
SOME PEOPLE CALL IT THE 3:00 IN
THE MORNING THOUGHT.
OTHER PEOPLE CALL IT THE
WITCHING HOUR, WHEN YOU WAKE UP
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT WITH
THAT THOUGHT THAT'S BEEN
WEIGHING ON YOU.
FOR THE VAST MAJORITY OF US WHEN
WE WAKE UP IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
NIGHT THINKING THAT THOUGHT IT
IS NEVER THROUGH THE LENS OF THE
PARTY WITH WHICH WE'RE
REGISTERED TO VOTE.
FOR THE VAST MAJORITY OF US WHEN
WE WAKE UP THINKING THAT THOUGHT
IT IS NEVER THROUGH THE LENS OF
SOME SIMPLISTIC DEMOGRAPHIC A
POLLSTER PUT US IN.
FOR THE VAST MAJORITY OF US WHEN
WE WAKE UP THINKING THAT THOUGHT
IT USUALLY HAS TO DO WITH ONE OF
JUST A VERY FEW THINGS, OUR
PERSONAL HEALTH, THE HEALTH OF
OUR CHILDREN, OUR PARENTS, FOR
SO MANY AMERICANS CAN I GET A
JOB, KEEP A JOB, PAY THE BILLS
BY THE END OF THE MONTH, RETIRE
WITH DIGNITY, FOR OUR STUDENTS
CAN I PAY OFF THOSE STUDENT
LOANS?
FOR SO MANY FAMILIES IN AMERICA,
CAN I HELP MY FAMILY MEMBER GET
OFF THEIR OPIOID ADDICTION?
THE VAST MAJORITY OF US HAVE SO
MUCH MORE IN COMMON THAN WHAT
SEPARATES US.
AND WHILE THERE ARE THESE
POWERFUL FORCES THAT ARE TRYING
TO SOW HATE AND DIVISION AMONG
US AND HAVE US POINT FINGERS AT
EACH OTHER AND OH, YOU'RE THAT,
AND I'M THIS, I SAY I'M NOT
BUYING IT.
I'M NOT BUYING IT.
AND THAT'S HOW I THINK ABOUT MY
EXPERIENCES.
I KNOW HOW MUCH WE HAVE IN
COMMON.
AND RIGHT NOW OUR COUNTRY
REQUIRES LEADERS AND THE TOP
LEADER TO INSTEAD OF USING A
MICROPHONE, IN A WAY THAT IS
ABOUT FUELING THE FAN OF HATE,
INSTEAD OF USING THE BULLY
PULPIT OF THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES, IN A WAY THAT IS
ABOUT TALKING ABOUT, WELL, ON
BOTH SIDES THERE'SM MERIT.
WE NEED A PRESIDENT WHO HAS
THROUGH PERSONAL EXPERIENCE AND
IDEALS, WE NEED LEADERSHIP THAT
UNDERSTANDS THE VAST MAJORITY OF
US HAVE SO MUCH MORE IN COMMON
THAN WHAT SEPARATES US AND
THEY'VE GOT TO STOP DIVIDING US.
THAT'S■8■8 I RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT.
THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT DIVISION,
AND I THINK THIS FALLS INTO THAT
CATEGORY.
YOU HAVE RECENTLY SAID IT WOULD
BE A TRAP, IT WOULD BE A MISTAKE
FOR DEMOCRATS TO FALL INTO A
TRAP OF A CONVERSATION ABOUT
WINNING BACK "THE GUY IN THE
MIDWEST WHICH IS CODE," WHAT IS
IT CODE FOR?
>> THERE IS A CONVERSATION
THAT'S BEEN HAPPENING AMONG MANY
PEOPLE, INCLUDING PUNDITS, THAT
SUGGEST -- I DON'T MEAN YOU.
>> I DIDN'T THINK SO, BUT THANKS
FOR CLARIFYING.
>> I JUST MEANT ON TV.
I'LL JUST KEEP DIGGING MYSELF
INTO THIS.
THINK WILL BE TALKING ABOUT MY
PERFORMANCE TONIGHT, THOSE SAME
PUNDITS.
IN ANY EVENT THERE'S A
CONVERSATION ALL OF US HAVE BEEN
HEARING ABOUT -- ESPECIALLY THE
2020 ELECTION, WHICH IS A
CONVERSATION SAYING, OH, WHO CAN
TALK TO THE PERSON IN THE
MIDWEST?
OH, WHO'S -- AND I REJECT THAT
NOTION THAT YOU HAVE ONE
CONVERSATION WITH SOMEONE IN THE
MIDWEST AND ANOTHER CONVERSATION
WITH SOMEBODY IN THE SOUTH AND
ANOTHER CONVERSATION WITH PEOPLE
WHO LIVE ON THE COAST.
I REJECT THAT NOTION AND I THINK
IT IS -- IT IS -- IT IS
SHORTSIGHTED.
AND IT IS ACTUALLY NOT CONNECTED
WITH WHERE PEOPLE REALLY ARE.
THE AMERICAN PUBLIC DON'T WANT
THAT.
THEY DON'T WANT THAT.
SO THAT'S WHAT I MEANT BY THAT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S BRING IN KIMBERLY
MORROW, A SENIOR STUDYING
POLITICS WORKING FULL-TIME WHILE
ATTENDING SCHOOL AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF NEW HAMPSHIRE MAN
>> GOOD EVENING, SENATOR.
THROUGH MY STUDIES AS A POLITICS
AND SOCIETY MAJOR AT UNH
MANCHESTER I'VE LEARNED WOMEN IN
OUR COUNTRY FACE VERY REAL
INEQUALITIES.
WHAT DO YOU PLAN TO DO AS
PRESIDENT TO LEVEL THE PLAYING
FIELD AND EMPOWER WORKING WOMEN?
>> ON DAY ONE WE NEED TO PASS
THE RA, THE EQUAL RIGHTS
AMENDMENT.
WE ALSO NEED TO SPEAK LOUDER
ABOUT THE REALITIES OF THE
FACTS, JUST AS YOU'VE DONE NOW
AND THANK YOU FOR YOUR
LEADERSHIP ON THIS.
BECAUSE IT IS JUST SOMETHING
THAT HAS TO BE ACKNOWLEDGED AND
DEALT WITH.
WOMEN ARE PAID ON AVERAGE 77% TO
THE DOLLAR.
AND THEN IF YOU LOOK AT
AFRICAN-AMERICAN WOMEN AND
LATINAS, EVEN LESS FOR DOING THE
SAME WORK.
YOU LOOK AT THE FACT THAT WE
HAVE A REAL BATTLE IN THIS
COUNTRY AROUND MINIMUM WAGE AND
THE NEED TO INCREASE MINIMUM
WAGE.
WE SHOULD UNDERSTAND MINIMUM
WAGE IS AMIN MUM STANDARD OF
LIVING BUT FEDERAL MINIMUM WAGE
IS $7.25 AVERAGING $15,000 A
YEAR AND THEN THE MAJORITY OF
WOMEN ARE MINIMUM WAGE WORKERS.
LET'S LOOK AT THE ISSUE OF WHAT
WE NEED TO DO AROUND DISPARITIES
AROUND ISSUES LIKE CHILD CARE,
UNDERSTANDING WOMEN ARE THE
PRIMARY CAREGIVER TO CHILDREN
AND YET WE DON'T HAVE A NATIONAL
POLICY AROUND AFFORDABLE CHILD
CARE, WHICH I AM A PROPONENT OF.
WE NEED TO ALSO ADDRESS WHAT IS
HAPPENING IN TERMS OF
UNDERSTANDING THAT WOMEN'S
ISSUES TO THE POINT OF BEING
MARGINALIZED HAVE TO BE BROUGHT
TO THE FOREFRONT AND WE SHOULD
ALSO
WHEN IN FACT THE REALITY IS WHEN
YOU LIFT UP THE ECONOMIC STATUS
OF WOMEN, YOU LIFT UP THE
ECONOMIC STATUS OF FAMILIES AND
COMMUNITIES AND ALL OF SOCIETY.
THAT'S HOW I FEEL ABOUT THAT.
>> MATTHEW SOLOMON IS FROM
MASSACHUSETTS.
A JUNIOR STUDYING POLITICS AND
PEACE AND JUSTICE.
HE'S ALSO THE PRESIDENT OF THE
LGBTQ ALLIANCE.
>> SO MY QUESTION IS IF ELECTED
PRESIDENT, WHAT KIND OF
PROTECTIONS, SPECIFIC
PROTECTIONS WILL YOU BE
EPROVIDING FOR THE LGBTQ PLUS
COMMUNITY AND MEMBERS OF COLOR?
>> SO I HAVE MY ENTIRE CAREER
AND LIFE BEEN AN ALLY OF THE
LGBTQ COMMUNITY AND I WILL SAY
WE MUST HAVE A COUNTRY THAT
AGREE NO GROUP SHOULD BE TREATED
WITHOUT EQUALITY UNDER THE LAW.
AND RIGHT NOW THAT IS THE CASE.
ON DAY ONE WOULD PASS THE
EQUALITY ACT TO MAKE SURE THAT
WE ACTUALLY CORRECT WHAT IS
WRONG AND GIVE LGBTQ PEOPLE
EQUAL RIGHTS UNDER THE LAW.
THIS IS A CIVIL RIGHTS AND HUMAN
RIGHTS ISSUE.
ER I WAS, AS ATTORNEY GENERAL,
IT WAS ONE OF THE PIVOTAL ISSUES
IN MY RACE TO BECOME ATTORNEY
GENERAL.
WHETHER OR NOT THE ELECTED
ATTORNEY GENERAL WOULD DEFEND AN
UNCONSTITUTIONAL LAW WHICH
DENIES SAME-SEX COUPLES THE
RIGHT TO MARRY.
PROP 8 WENT TO THE UNITED STATES
SUPREME COURT.
WE WENT AND THE WEDDING BELLS
RANG ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
I'M VERY PROUD OF THAT.
IN 2004 O, WHEN THE CHATTER
AMONG A LOT OF DEMOCRATS WAS
ABOUT CIVIL UNION, I WAS
MARRYING SAME-SEX COUPLES AT SAN
FRANCISCO CITY HALL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I WILL TELL YOU YOU'LL REMEMBER
THE TRAGIC CASES INVOLVING
TRANSGENDER MEN WHO WERE KILLED
AND THERE WAS THIS DEFENSE THAT
WAS HAPPENING IN COURT WHERE THE
MURDER WAS ARE CALLING IT THE
GAY PANIC DFLS.
OH, I PANICKED BECAUSE HE WAS
GAY AND THEREFORE SHOULD NOT BE
CONVICTED OF MURDER.
IT WAS HAPPENING AROUND THE
MATTHEW SHEPHERD CASE.
WHEN I WAS KNOWING THIS WAS
HAPPENING, I BROUGHT DA'S FROM
AROUND THE CURRENTRY TO SAN
FRANCISCO WHERE I HOSTED AND
CREATED A TRAINING FOR
PROSECUTORED AROUND THE CAN
COUNTRY ON HOW TO DEFEAT THE GAY
PANIC DEFENSE.
ON THE ISSUE OF TRANSGENDER
ROI
RIGHTS, RIGHT NOW IN PARTICULAR
WE HAVE A PRESIDENT WHO IS
REVIVING -- THE COURT SAID NO
AND NOW WE HAVE A PRESIDENT WHO
IS PUTTING IN PLACE A PROCESS
FOR DISCHARGING TRANSGENDER MEN
AND WOMEN WHO HAVE MADE
COMMITMENT TO OUR COUNTRY AND TO
DEFEND OUR DEMOCRACY AT GREAT
SERVICE AND POTENTIAL SACRIFICE
AND THIS PRESIDENT WANTS TO KICK
THEM OUT OF THE MILITARY BECAUSE
THEY ARE TRANSGENDER.
IT IS ABOSOLUTELY UNCONSCIONABLE
AND THAT IS SOMETHING I WOULD
REVERSE IMMEDIATELY WHEN I AM
ELECTED PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES.
>> I WANT TO BRING IN RACHEL, A
SOPHOMORE AT HARVARD FROM CAN
CO.
COLORADO.
>> THE PAST COUPLE OF YEARS HAVE
SEEN YOUNG PEOPLE GETTING
INVOLVED IN POLITICS AND
ACTIVISM, ORGSINIZING AROUND GUN
CONTROL AND CLIMATE CHANGE.
GIVEN THAT POLICIES WILL EFFECT
PEOPLE FOR YEARS TO COME, DO YOU
THINK AMERICANS HAVE A RIGHT TO
VOTE AT AGE 16?
>> I THINK THERE IS NO QUESTION
IF WE ARE LOOKING AT WHAT IS
GOING ON IN OUR COUNTRY, WE'RE
PUTTING MORE RESPONSIBILITIES ON
PEOPLE AT YOUNG AGE THE LARGERER
NUMBER OF PEOPLE WE CAN INVOLVE
IN THE ELECTORAL PROCESS, YI
THINK THE MORE ROBUST IT WOULD
BE.
I THINK ONE OF THE DOWN SIDES
BUT THANK YOU DO CNN FOR DOING
THE TOWN HALL WITH STUDENTS IS
IF THEY DON'T WRITE CHECKS, THEY
DON'T GET HEARD.
I BELIEVE STRONGLY YOU CAN JAUJ
SOCIETY BASED ON HOW IT TREATS
ITS CHILDREN.
YOU CAN LOOK AT WHAT WE ARE NOT
DOING FOR STUDENTS, TEENAGERS
AND YOUNGER.
AND I BELIEVE IF THEY HAD
GREATER POLITICAL POWER, MAYBE
WE WOULD GET OUR ACT TOGETHER
BETTER THAN WE'VE BEEN DOING AND
MAYBE THAT'S ONE OFF THE STEPS
TOWARDS IT.
AND WHAT I'M SO EXCITED ABOUT
AND I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN HERE FOR
LIKE FIVE HOURS, IS THAT ONE OF
THE THINGS THAT IS SO -- THAT WE
HAVE TO REMEMBER ABOUT THE
HISTORY OF OUR COUNTRY, IT'S
SOME OF THE GREATEST MOVEMENT
THAT HAVE BROUGHT ABOUT CHANGE,
SOCIAL CHANGE, ADVANCEMENT,
PROGRESS HAVE BEEN FUELLED AND
BORN FROM OUR STUDENTS.
>> THANK YOU, SENATOR.
SO WE WANT TO THANK SENATOR
KAMALA HARRIS.
THAT IS FOUR TOWN HALLS DOWN.
ONE NEAR GO.
WHEN WE COME BACK, ANDERSON
COOPER IS GOING TO BE HERE.
OUR FINAL PRESIDENTIAL TOWN HALL
OF THE NIGHT.
Introducing the all-new
2019 Ford Ranger,
It's the right gear.
With a Terrain Management
System for... this.
A bash plate for... that.
An Electronic Locking Rear
Differential for...
Yeah... this.
Heading to the supermarket?
Get any truck.
Heading out here?
Get the Ford Ranger.
The only adventure gear
Built Ford Tough.
♪♪
Every day,
visionaries are creating
the future.
♪♪
So, every day,
we put our latest technology
and unrivaled network to work.
♪♪
The United States
Postal Service makes
more e-commerce
deliveries to homes
than anyone else
in the country.
♪♪
Because the future only
happens with people
who really know how
to deliver it.
Because the future only
happens with people
♪♪
Applebee's Bigger, Bolder
Grill Combos.
Now that's Eatin Good
in the Neighborhood.
♪♪
It's nice.
You got this!
♪♪
WOO!