>>> HAPPENING NOW, BREAKING
NEWS.
TALKING IMPEACHMENT.
HOUSE DEMOCRATIC CAUCUS IS ON
THE PHONE RIGHT NOW, DISCUSSING
THE MUELLER REPORT AND WHETHER
TO MOVE FORWARD ON TRYING TO
REMOVE PRESIDENT TRUMP FROM
OFFICE.
THIS COMES JUST HOURS BEFORE
FIVE PROMINENT PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES WILL BE ASKED ABOUT
IT DURING A CNN TOWN HALL EVENT.
WE'RE STANDING BY TO FIND OUT
WHAT DEMOCRATS WILL DECIDE ON
IMPEA
IMPEACHMENT.
>>> TRUMP SUES CONGRESS.
THE PRESIDENT REMAINS DEFIANT AS
HIS LAWYERS GO TO COURT TO BLOCK
CONGRESSIONAL INVESTIGATIONS OF
HIS FINANCES.
WHY DOESN'T HEP WANT CONGRESS TO
TALK TO HIS ACCOUNTANTS?
AND WILL A FEDERAL COURT STOP
CONGRESS FROM FOLLOWING THE
MONEY?
>>> CAIN UNABLE.
HERMAN CAIN FACING SCATHIE
HERMAN CAIN FACING ING BACKLASH
HIS CONDUCT.
>>> AND INSPIRED BY ISIS.
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE ARE DEAD
INCLUDING AT LEAST FOUR
AMERICANS AFTER SUICIDE BOMBERS
TARGET CHURCHES AND HOTELS
OVERSEAS.
TONIGHT, A U.S. INTELLIGENCE
ASSESSMENT SAYS THOSE
RESPONSIBLE LIKELY WERE INSPIRED
BY ISIS.
WHY WERE URGENT WARNINGS
IGNORED?
I'M WOLF BLITZER.
YOU'RE IN "THE SITUATION ROOM".■
>> THIS IS CNN BREAKING NEWS.
>> ROOER FOLLOWING BREAKING
NEWS.
RIGHT NOW HOUSE DEMOCRATS ARE
HOLDING AN URGENT CONFERENCE
CALL TO DISCUSS THEIR STRATEGY
FOLLOWING THE RELEASE OF THE
MUELLER REPORT.
PART OF THAT STRATEGY INCLUDES
THE POSSIBILITY OF KBEECHING
PRESIDENT TRUMP BECAUSE OF WHAT
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL REVEALED
ABOUT THE PRESIDENT'S REPEATED
ATTEMPTS TO INTERVIEW WITH AND
SHUT DOWN THE INVESTIGATION.
THE PRESIDENT INSISTS HE ISN'T
WORRIED ABOUT IMPEACHMENT.
HE ALSO IS SUING CONGRESS RIGHT
NOW, CONTENDING LAWMAKERS DON'T
HAVE A RIGHT TO LOOK INTO HIS
FINAN
FINANCIAL DEALINGS.
THE U.S. SENATE HAS THE FINAL
SAY ON IMPEACHMENT.
I'LL SPEAK WITH DEMOCRATIC
SENATOR, JACK REED, AND I'LL GET
TO THAT MOMENTARILY.
AND OUR CORRESPONDENTS AND
ANALYSTS, THEY WILL HAVE FULL
COVERAGE OF THE DAY'S TOP
STORIES.
>>> FIRST, THE POLITICS OF
IMPEACHMENT.
OUR SENIOR CONGRESSIONAL
CORRESPONDENT, MANU RAJU, IS UP
ON CAPITOL HILL, KEEPING TABS ON
SOURCES LISTENING IN ON THE
DEMOCRATS' CONFERENCE CALL.
MANU, I ALSO UNDERSTAND, YOU
HAVE SOME BREAKING NEWS.
>> Reporter: YEAH, BREAKING NEWS
INDEED, WOLF.
THE HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE IS
SUBPOENAING THE FORMER WHITE
HOUSE COUNSEL, DON McGAHN,
ASKING HIM FOR HIS TESTIMONY AND
FOR RECORDS, IN RELATION TO THE
COMMITTEE'S INVESTIGATION INTO
POTENTIAL OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE.
THIS, ACCORDING TO A PERSON
FAMILIAR WITH THE MATTER, WHO
TELLS ME THAT THE COMMITTEE IS,
INDEED, MOVING FORWARD WITH A
SUBPOENA FOR DON McGAHN.
RECALL THAT RECENTLY, THE
COMMITTEE WASZED TO
ISSUE SUBPOENAS FOR FIVE
DIFFERENT INDIVIDUALS.
FIVE FORMER WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIALS, PEOPLE WHO HAD
COOPERATED WITH THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION.
WELL, IN THE AFTERMATH OF THE
RELEASE OF THE REDACTED VERSION
OF THE MUELLER REPORT, THE
COMMITTEE IS MAKING ITS NEXT
MOVE, ISSUING A SUBPOENA FOR DON
McGAHN, ASKING FOR HIS
TESTIMONY, PROBABLY IN PUBLIC.
ALSO, ASKING FOR RECORDS,
ANYTHING THAT HE GOT AS HE
PREPARED TO TESTIFY.
AND AS YOU KNOW, WOLF, McGAN WAS
A CENTRAL PLAYER FOR THE --
DURING THE FIRST TWO YEARS OF
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION AND HIS
NAME IS MENTIONED THROUGHOUT
ROBERT MUELLER'S REPORT, IN
ADDITION NO WHAT HE'S REFERENCED
IN THE REPORT, TO THE
PRESIDENT'S EFFORTS TO
APPARENTLY TRY AND DISMISS
ROBERT MUELLER.
HE WAS ASKED TO DISMISS ROBERT
MUELLER, BUT McGAN, ACCORDING TO
THE REPORT, RESISTED THAT MOVE.
AND SAID THAT HE WOULD RATHER
RESIGN THAN TRIGGER WHAT HE
REGARDED AS A POTENTIAL SATURDAY
NIGHT MASSACRE.
THAT'S HOW THE MUELLER REPORT
QUOTES DON McGAHN'S VIEWS IN
RESISTING THE CALL TO FIRE THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL.
BUT NEVERTHELESS, A SIGNIFICANT
MOVE HERE BY THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE, TAKING STEPS TO
SUBPOENA THE FORMER WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL, DON McGAHN, AND EXPECT
THAT TO HAPPEN POTENTIAL SOON.
WE'LL SEE THE EXACT DATE, WHEN
THEY EXPECT THEM TO COME
FORWARD.
BUT THE MOMENT, JERRY NADLER
TELLING HIS COLLEAGUES ON THIS
CONFERENCE CALL THAT THAT'S WHAT
HE PLANS TO DO WITH HIS
COMMITTEE, AS THE DEMOCRATIC
LEADERSHIP TRIES TO MOVE FORWARD
ON THE INVESTIGATIVE FRONT AND
TRIES TO TAMP DOWN CALLS FOR
IMPEACHMENT, SAYING THEY CAN
JUST AS MUCH INFORMATION BY
INTERVIEWING PEOPLE LIKE DON
McGAHN AND NOT NECESSARILY GOING
THE ROUTE OF IMPEACHMENT, AT
LEAST NOT YET.
BUT NEVERTHELESS, IT COULD BE A
VERY DRAMATIC MOMENT IF DON
McGAHN COMES TO CONGRESS AND
TELLS HIS WOLF.
>> HE SPENT 30 YOURS<RI
QUESTIONS FROM THE Mx
WHY DID÷ THEY NEED TO IMPEACHO N
McG
WHY WOULDN'T HE JUST COME
VOLUNTARILY?
>> IT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
WE'VE KNOWN THAT THEY'VE HAD
INTERACTIONS WITH DON McGAHN'S
ATTORNEY SINCE MARCH.
THE ATTORNEY HAS SENT LETTERS TO
81 INDIVIDUALS AND ENTITIES WHO
THEY WANT TO DISCUSS AS PART OF
THE DEMOCRATS' INVESTIGATION
INTO POTENTIAL OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE, POTENTIAL ABUSES IN THE
WHITE HOUSE.
DON McGAHN WAS ONE OF THOSE
INDIVIDUALS.
NOW, IT'S NOT CLEAR IF HE HAS
FULLY COMPLIED WITH THE REQUEST.
WE KNOW THAT FORMER WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIALS HAVE DEFERRED TO THE
WHITE HOUSE AND SAY, YOU NEED TO
GO THROUGH THE WHITE HOUSE TO
DETERMINE WHAT CONSTITUTES
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE AND WHAT
DOES NOT.
SO IT'S UNCLEAR WHETHER OR NOT
HE HAS PROVIDED THE SAME
INFORMATION TO CAPITOL HILL THAT
HE HAS PROVIDED TO THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL AND THE DEMOCRATS
BELIEVE THAT, ESSENTIALLY,
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE RIGHTS ARE
WAIVED BECAUSE OF THE WAY THAT
DOCUMENTS WERE EXCHANGED BETWEEN
THE WHITE HOUSE AND DON McGAHN'S
ATTORNEYS AND THE WAY HE
PREPARED TO TESTIFY BEFORE THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL.
THEY'LL TRY TO PURSUE IT ON
THOSE GROUNDS.
WE'LL SEE IF DON McGAHN COMPLIES
COMPLETELY.
PERHAPS THEY'LL DROP THEIR
SUBPOENA IF THERE'S A VOLUNTARY
AGREEMENT.
BUT AT THE MOMENT, THAT'S A
PRETTY SIGNIFICANT MOVE TO TRY
TO COMPEL DON McGAHN'S TESTIMONY
AND RYE TO GET HIM TO PROVIDE
RECORDS PART OF THIS
CREDIBILITY WHEN HE WASxTICE,
ANSWERING Qxxxxxx xx
MUELLER TEAMS I , 30 HOURS, HE
SPENT■■■ HE ALSO TO PROVIDE
DO TO THE xE?
AND ARE THERE DATES WHEN THEY
WANT HIM TO APPEAR?
>> YEAH, WE'RE BEING TOLD THAT
DOCUMENTS BY MAY 7th, TESTIMONY
BY MAY 21st.
SO THAT IS JUST A FEW WEEKS
AWAY, WOLF.
SO MAY COULD BE SET UP FOR A
VERY SIGNIFICANT MONTH FOR THIS
COMMITTEE.
BECAUSE MAY 2nd IS WHEN BILL
BARR IS EXPECTED TO COME IN A
PUBLIC HEARING BEFORE THE HOUSE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE.
THAT SAME MONTH, JERRY NADLER
WANTS TO BRING IN THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL TO TESTIFY, AS WELL.
THERE'S NO DATE SET YET FOR THE
MUELLER HEARING, BUT MAY 7th IS
WHEN HE WANTS DOC
OVER
MA 21 I WHEN HE WANTS THAT
McGAHN TESTIMONY.
SO SIGNIFICANT DEVELOPMENTS
COULD HAPPEN.
WE'LL SEE WHAT THEY ULTIMATELY
LEARN.
BUT A SIGN THAT THE DEMOCRATS
AGAIN WANT TO GO DOWN THIS ROUTE
OF INVESTIGATING AND LOOKING
FURTHER INTO WHAT EXACTLY THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL FOUND, NOT
NECESSARILY GOING DOWN THE ROUTE
OF DEBATING ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENT AND TRYING TO REMOVE
THE PRESIDENT FROM OFFICE, BUT
CONTINUE ON THIS FRONT.
WE'LL SEE IF McGAHN PROVIDES THE
DEMOCRATS WITH WHAT THEY'RE
ASKING FOR HERE, WOLF.
>> I THINK THEY WANT MUELLER TO
TESTIFY BY MAY 23rd, AROUND THAT
TIME, AS WELL.
BY THE END OF THIS MONTH.
THE ISSUE OF IMPEACHMENT SEEMS
TO HAVE THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
PRETTY DEEPLY DIVIDED RIGHT NOW.
I UNDERSTAND THEY'RE DISCUSSING
THAT RIGHT NOW IN THIS HOUSE
DEMOCRATIC CONFERENCE CALL.
WHAT ARE YOU LEARNING?
>> YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
NANCY PELOSI HAS MADE IT PRETTY
CLEAR THAT SHE IS NOT EAGER TO
GO THIS ROUTE ON IMPEACHMENT.
EVEN AS CALLS ON THE LEFT ARE
GROWING LOUDER TO IMPEACH, SHE
SAYS THERE ARE OTHER WAYS TO
LEARN ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED HERE.
AND S■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■       O
HER COLLEAGUES              ■■■G
THE PRESIDE■■■■■■■■■ ■■ ■■■■ ■■■
GAINED■■■ ■■■■■■■UTSIDE■■■■■■■■
NEEDED REFORMS■■■■■■■■■■CT OUR
DEMOCRACY, WE MUST SHOW THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
PRESENTATION OF FACT.
AND THAT LINE RIGHT THERE, THAT
THEY CAN LEARN ABOUT THESE FACTS
OUTSIDE OF IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDINGS, A REAL SIGN OF WHAT
HER PREFERENCE IS.
SO THE QUESTION ON THIS CALL
RIGHT NOW, WOLF, IS HOW MANY OF
HER COLLEAGUES AGREE.
I'M WILLING TO BET THAT MOST A
LOT OF THEM DO, BUT THERE WILL
STILL BE CALLS TO URGE THEIR
CAUCUS TO TAKE A DIFFERENT
APPROACH, BUT SHE AT THE MOMENT
IS SAYING, LET'S SLOW DOWN, TALK
ABOUT IMPEACHMENT, AND STILL DO
THINGS LIKE WHAT JERRY NADLER IS
DOING, LIKE ISSUING A SUBPOENA
FOR THE FORMER WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL AND GET HIS TESTIMONY AS
THEY PURSUE THEIR NEXT STEPS,
WOLF.
>> THESE AREx]x]x]x]x]x]x]x]x]x
DEVELOPMENTS UNFOLDI■
MANU,OU V■
LET'S GO TO OUR CHIEF WHITE
HOUSE CORRESPONDENT, JIM ACOSTA.
JIM, THE PRESIDENT WON'T BE
TESTIFYI ASSUMING HE DOES.
eporter: THAT'S RIGH WOLF.
AND KEEP IN MIND, DON McGAHN THE
THE FORMER SENIOR WHITE HOUSE
OFFICI WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL WHO WAS TOLD BY THE
PRESIDENT TO FIRE THE2ELLER.
McGAORDING TO THE MUELLER
REEFUSED TO DO THAT, AS  WAS SA
TRIGGER A SATURDAY NIGHT
MASSACRE.
AND THAT IS GOING TO BE SOME
PRETTY FASCINATING TELEVISION TO
WATCH, IF THE FORMER WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL TESTIFIES UP ON CAPITOL
HILL IN FRONT OF THE HOUSE
THAT■C WITH THE
PRESIDENT, IT IS GOING TO BE
SOMETHING THAT THE ENTIRE
COUNTRY IS GOING TO WANT TO
WATCH.
MEANWHILE, THE PRESIDENT, WE
SHOULD SAY, HAS BEEN TRYING TO
CONVINCE THE PUBLIC ALL DAY LONG
TO BELIEVE HIM AND NOT THE
MUELLER REPORT.
THE PRESIDENT INSISTED TODAY
THAT HIS AIDES ALWAYS OBEY HIS
ORDERS, DESPITE WHAT THE MUELLER
REPORT SAYS ABOUT THAT
INTERACTION WITH DON McGAHN AND
OTHER INTERACT.
JUST TODAY, I WAS TOLD BY A
FORMER WSE OFFICIAL THAT
THERE WEREICIALS LIKE DON
McGAHN WHO■C■C REFUSED TO CARRY
THE PRESIDENT'S ORDERS.
AND THE PRESIDENT ALSO CLAIMING
HE'S NOT WORRIED ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT TONIGHT,
HE TWEETED ABOUT THAT PROSPECT
EARLIER TODAY.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
EVERYBODY.
HAPPY EASTER.
>> Reporter: AT THE WHITE HOUSE
EASTER EGG ROLL, PRESIDENT TRUMP
TOLD CNN HIS ORDERS ARE ALWAYS
FOLLOWED.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED THAT YOU
STAFF IS IGNORING YOUR ORDERS AS
THE MUELLER REPORT PORTRAYS?
>> NOBODY DISOBEYS MY ORDERS.
>> Reporter: BUT SPECIAL COUNSEL
ROBERT MUELLER'S REPORT SAYS
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL WROTE IN HIS
REPORT, THE PRESIDENT'S EFFORTS
TO INFLUENCE THE INVESTIGATION
WERE MOSTLY UNSUCCESSFUL, BUT
THAT IS LARGELY BECAUSE THE
PERSONS WHO SURROUNDED THE
PRESIDENT DECLINEDRY OUT
ORDERS.
DEMOCRATS WANT TO HEAR FROM
FORMER WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL DON
McGAHN, AFTER IT WAS STATED IN
THE MUELLER REPORT THAT HE
REFUSED TO REQUEST BY THE
PRESIDENT TO FIRE THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL.
WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS INSIST,
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH SUCH
AN ORDER.
>> IF THE PRESIDENT WANTED TO
FIRE BOB MUELLER, HE WOULD HAVE.
IN OTHER WORDS, HE HAS THE
AUTHORITY TO DO THAT.
HE FIRED DIRECTOR COMEY.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT ALSO
APPEARS TO BE LAYING OUT THE
CASE AGAINST HIS OWN
IMPEACHMENT, TWEETING, ONLY HIGH
CRIMES AND MISDEMEANORS CAN LEAD
TO IMPEACHMENT.
THERE WERE NO CRIMES BY ME, NO
COLLUSION, NO OBSTRUCTION, SO
YOU CAN IMPEACH.
IT WAS THE DEMOCRATS THAT■y
COMMITTED THE CRIMES, YOUR
REPUBLICooAT EASTER EGG ROLL, T
PRESIDENT ALL BUT HOPPED AWAY
FROM THE IMPEACHMENT QUESTION,
TO>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT, PRESIDENT?
>> NOT EVEN A LITTLE BIT.
>> Repor PRESIDENT'S
OUTSIDE ATTORNEY IS ALSO
RESPONDING TO MUELLER'S
FINDINGS, ARGUING ON CNN THAT IT
WAS JUST FINE FOR THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN TO ACCEPT DIRT ON
HILLARY CLINTON FROM RUSSIA.
>> THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH
TAKING INFORMATION FROM
RUSSIANS!
>> THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH
TAKING INFORMATION --
>> DEPENDS ON WHERE IT CAME
FROM!
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS SAY,
THAT'S UNACCEPTABLE.
>> I TOTALLY DISAGREE WITH MR.
GIULIANI.
THERE IS A LOT WRONG WITH TAKING
INFORMATION FROM AN ADVERSARY, A
FOREIGN ADVERSARY, FOREIGN
GOVERNMENT.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER MAJOR
DEVELOPMENT IN THE
INVESTIGATION, THE TRUMP
ORGANIZATION IS NOW SUING HOUSE
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE ELIJAH
CUMMINGS TO BLOCK DEMOCRATS FROM
OBTAINING THE PRESIDENT'S
FINANCIAL STATEMENTS FOR THE
LAST EIGHT YEARS, SAYING IN A
STATEMENT, IT'S AN UNPRECEDENTED
OVERREACH OF CONGRESSIONAL
AUTHORITY.
CUMMINGS FIRED BACK SAYING, THE
PRESIDENT HAS A LONG HISTORY OF
TRYING TO USE BASELESS LAWSUITS
TO ATTACK HIS ADVERSARIES, BUT
THERE IS SIMPLY NO VALID LEGAL
BASIS.
THE PRESIDENT WAS KEEPING BUSY
ON TWITTER, ANNOUNCING FORMER
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE, HERMAN
CAIN, HAS DECIDED AGAINST
SEEKING A SPOT ON THE FEDERAL
RESERVE.
BUT THE PRESIDENT WAS HAVING
TROUBLE COMMUNICATING THE FACTS
ON THE TERRORIST ATTACKS IN SRI
LANKA.
AT ONE POINT, TWEHAT 138#
MILLION PEOPLE HAD ■
MR. TRUMP ALSO TWEETED, HE HAD
SPOKEN WITH THE PRESIDENT OF SRI
LANKA.
TURNS OUT IT WAS THATCOUNTRY'S
PRIME MINISTER.
AS FOR THE ■a■a■a■a ACTIONS
LAID OUT IN THE MUELLER REPORT,
A FORMER ADMINISTRATION OFFICIAL
SAYS MR. TRUMP, QUOTE, COULD
HAVE USED A LOT MORE FIRM LEGAL
GUIDANCE EARLY ON IN HIS
PRESIDENCY.
AND WE SHOULD POINT OUT LATE IN
THE DAY, THE PRESIDENT TWEETED
AGAIN ABOUT THE MUELLER REPORT,
SAYING STATING, ISN'T IT AMAZING
THE PEOPLE WHO WERE CLOSEST TO
ME BY FAR AND KNEW THE CAMPAIGN
BETTER THAN ANYONE WERE NEVER
EVEN CALLED TO TESTIFY BEFORE
MUELLER.
IT'S NOT CLEAR WHO THE PRESIDENT
IS REFERRING TO IN THAT TWEET,
WOLF, BUT TOP AIDES TO THE EVEN
SON-IN-LAW, JARED KUSHNER, WERE
INTERVIEWED BY THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL.
THE PRESID SEEM■ç
AGAIN TWISTING THE TRUTH TO
UNDERMINE THE MUELLER REPORT.
WOLF?
>> JIM ACOSTA AT THE WHITE HOUSE
FOR US, THANK YOU.
JOINING US NOW, SENATOR JACK
REED OF RHODE ISLAND.
HE'S THE TOP DEMOCRAT ON THE
ARMED SERVICES COMMITTEE AND AS
SUCH, IS AN EXMEMB OF THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE THANK YOU
SO MUCH FOR JOINING US.
>> THANK YOU, WOLF.
>> WE HAVE A LOT TO DISCUSS, BUT
FIRST, YOUR REACTION TO THIS
SUBPOENA TO HAVE DON McGAHN TO
COME BEFORE THE COMMITTEE AND
TESTIFY.
WHAT'S YOUR REACTION?
>> I THINK IT'S APPROPRIATE.
I THINK THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE IS THE FOCAL POINT,
THE FOCUS OF INVESTIGATIONS OF
THE PRESIDENT'S CONDUCT.
MR. McGAN WAS THERE.
HE IS FEATURES PROMINENTLY IN
THE MUELLER REPORT.
I THINK IT WOULD BE APPROPRIATE
FOR NOT ONLY THE CONGRESS, BUT
FOR THE AMERICAN PEOPLE TO HEAR
HIS POSITION ON WHAT HE SAID,
IT'S BEING DISPUTED BY THE
PRESIDENT.
I TEND TO CONCUR WITH THE
MUELLER REPORT.
I THINK DIRECTOR MUELLER DID A
VERY FAIR, VERY HONEST, VERY
PROFESSIONAL JOB.
>> SOME ARE ALREADY EVEN MAKING
COMPARISONS TO WATERGATE, WHEN
THEN WHITE HOUSE COUNCIL JOHN
DEAN WAS FORCED TO COME BEFORE
CONGRESS AND TESTIFY.
DO YOU SEE ANY PARALLELS HERE?
>> WELL, I THINK THERE ARE
PARALLELS IN THE SENSE THAT MR.
McGAHN WAS PRIVYV■r TO A LOT OFE
ISSUES SURROUNDING, PARTICULARLY
THE OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE
CHARGES, WHERE THE INFERENCE WAS
THE PRESIDENT WAS TAKING STEPS
REPEATEDLY OR TRYING TO TAKE
STEPS TO FRUSTRATE THE
INVESTIGATION.
FIRING COMEY AND DOING OTHER
THINGS.
AND MR. McGAHN WAS THE COUNSEL
TO THE PRESIDENT AND WAS CLOSELY
INVOLVED IN THOSE DECISIONS.
AND I THINK IT WOULD BE FAIR FOR
HIM, NOT ONLY FAIR, IT WOULD BE
APPROPRIATE FOR HIM TO COME
BEFORE THE CONGRESS AND THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
AND I THINK HE WOULD ANSWER
TRUTHFULLY.
I THINK HE'S A VERY EXCELLENT
ATTORNEY AND A VERY DECENT
PERSON AND HE WILLDDWER
TRUTHFULLY.
AND THOSE ANSWERS, I THINK, WILL
HELP.
>> ASD WE SPEAK, SENATOR, YOUR
DEMOCRATIC COLLEAGUES IN THE
HOUSRE A CONFERENCE
CALL DIS THIS ENTIRE
ON OF IMPEACHMENT.
BASED ON YOUR READING
MUELLER REPORT, DO YOU BELIEVE
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS COMMITTED
IMPEACHABLE OFFENSES?
>> I THINK THE QUESTION ABOUT
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE IS STILL
ONE THAT HAS TO BE LOOKED AT
VERY CLOSELY.
AS EVEN ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR
SAID, IN HIS LETTER TO US
INITIALLY, MR. MUELLER COULD NOT
EXONERATE THE PRESIDENT FROM
THAT CHARGE.
SO THAT IS A VERY SIGNIFICANT
ISSUE.
WITH RESPECT TO THE CONSPIRAC
ISSUE, THE BARR LETTER SUGGESTED
THAT THERE WAS NOTHING THERE.
BUT WHEN IT CAME DOWN TO THE
OBSTRUCTION CHARGE, HE WAS VERY,
I THINK, SPECIFIC IN QUOTING
DIRECTLY FROM ALL OF THE REPORT
THAT HE COULD NOT BE EXONERATED.
THE PRESIDENT COULD NOT BE
EXONERATED.
SO I THINK YOU HAVE AN ISSUE
THERE.
AND I THINK THE BEST WAY TO
PROCEED IS THROUGH FURTHER
INVESTIGATION.
CALLING FIRST DIRECTOR MUELLER,
WHO CAN GIVE CONTEXT.
I MEAN, IF HIS WHOLE REPORT WAS
BASED ON THE PREMISE THAT HE
THOUGHT WAS APPROPRIATE, THAT HE
COULD NEVER CHARGE THE
PRESIDENT, BECAUSE THAT WAS A
POLICY OF THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT, THAT A PRESIDENT
CANNOT BE CHARGED, CAN ONLY BE
IMPEACHED, I THINK THAT PUTS
THIS WHOLE REPORT INTO A
SPECIFIC CONTEXT THAT WILL BE
VERY USEFUL.
AND THEN I THINK WE HAVE TO GET
THE WHOLE REPORT.
EVEN THE REDACTED PORTIONS.
IT COULD BE CONTROLLED IN TERMS
OF DISTRIBUTION, SO NOT EVERYONE
GETS TO SEE IT, BUT CRITICAL
MEMBERS ON BOTH SIDES OF THE
AISLE GET TO SEE IT.
AND I THINK WITH THE McGAHN
TESTIMONY, IT COULD BE -- IT
COD EVEN FURTHER LIGHT ON
WHAT TOOK
>> YOUR SENATE COLLEAGUE,
SENATOR ELIZABETH WARREN, A
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE FROM
MASSACHUSETTS, SHE'S CALLED ON
THE HOUSE TO BEGINMENT
PROCEEDINGS.
IS SHE RIGHT?
IS THAT NECESSARY RIGHT NOW?
>> AT THIS JUNCTURE, I THINK  A
THE INVESTIGATION.
THERE'S A CERTAIN POINT WHICH
THE EVIDENCE AND THE FACTS WILL
BECOME OBVIOUSLY, I THINK, TO
ALL, WE HOPE, BUT AT LEAST TO
SIGNIFICANT NUMBERS, THAT THERE
IS CULPABILITY HERE.
AND AT THAT POINT, THAT'S WHEN I
THINK THE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE IN
THE HOUSE CAN START FORMAL, IF
YOU WILL SAY, IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDINGS.
BUT THERE IS AN OBLIGATION TO
INVESTIGATE THESE ALLEGATIONS.
AND TO ESTABLISH THE FACTS,
ESTABLISH THE EVIDENCE.
AND AFTER THAT, IF YOU'VE
REACHED A CRITICAL POINT, AND
YOU FEEL THAT THERE HAVE BEEN
HIGH CRIMES AND MISDEMEANORS,
WHICH IS A VERY, VERY BROAD
RANGE OF POSSIBLE CHARGES HAVE
BEEN REACHED, THEN YOU CAN
PROCEED.
AND AGAIN, HAVING BEEN THROUGH
THIS ONCE BEFORE IN THE '90s,
THEN IT GOES TO THE FLOOR OF THE
HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES, AND
THAT'S THE VOTE OF THE HOUSE.
NO PRESIDENT IS IMPEACHED UNTIL
THE HOUSE, THE WHOLE HOUSE
VOTES.
SO THESE JUDICIARY PROCEEDINGS
ARE APPROPRIATE, USEFUL, AND I
THINK AT THE INVESTIGATION
LEVEL, ARE TIMELY AND SHOULD BE
PURSUED.
>> SENATOR REID, THANKOD US.
>> THANKS, WOLF!
>>> UP NEXT, WE'LL PREVIEW A
MAJOR POLITICAL EVENT.
CNN PRESIDENTIAL TOWN HALLS WITH
FIVE MAJOR DEMOCRATIC
CANDIDATES.
WHAT WILL THEY SAY ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT?
My experience with USAA
has been excellent.
They really appreciate
the military family
and it really shows.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
It was funny because
when we would call
another insurance company,
hey would say
“Oh we can't beat USAA”
We're the Webber family.
We're the Tenney's
We're the Hayles,
and we're USAA members for life.
♪
Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
[music playing]
(Michelle)
I know what it's like to be in a
financially struggling family.
We had a lot of
leftovers...[chuckles]
I couldn't have asked
for better parents,
but like most people they didn't
have anyone to teach them
the best financial habits.
So we changed that.
As a financial health coach,
I help people every day.
I try to put myself in their
shoes from my own experience.
I connect to them because
I've been there.
Helping families like mine
save a little money
changes everything.
This is personalized guidance.
This is Wells Fargo.
(Client's Voice)
Remember that degree
you got in taxation?
(Danny)
Of course you don't
because you didn't!
Your job isn't doing hard
work...
...it's making them do hard
...and getting paid for it.
(VO)
Snap and sort your expenses to
save over $4,600 at tax time.
QUICKBOOKS. BACKING YOU.
Great. Another wireless ad.
So many of them are full of this
complicated,
tricky language about their
network and offers
and blah blah blah blah blah
blah.
Look Sprint's gonna do things
differently,
and let you decide for yourself.
They're offering a new 100%
Total Satisfaction Guarantee.
Try it out and see the savings.
If you don't love it, get your
money back.
See? Simple.
Now Sprint's Unlimited Plan
comes with one of the newest
phones
included for just $35 a month.
So switch now.
>>> WE'RE FOLLOWING BREAKING
NEWS.
THE HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE
HAS JUST SUBPOENAED PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S FORMER WHITE HOUSE
COUNCIL, DON McGAHN.
McGAHN'S POSSIBLE TESTIMONY AND
THE POSSIBILITY OF IMPEACHING
PRESIDENT TRUMP ARE CERTAIN TO
COME UP AT TONIGHT'S CNN
PRESIDENTIAL TOWN HALLS.
JOINING US NOW FROM THE SITE OF
TONIGHT'S CNN TOWN HALL EVENT,
OUR SENIOR POLITICAL ANALYST,
MARK PRESTON, AND OUR
SSIONAL CORRESPONDENT,
PHIL MATTINGLY.
MARK, IMPEACHMENT CERTAINLY HAS
BEEN A HOTOPIC ALL ALONG.
WILL WE LEARN MORE TONIGHT ABOUT
WHERE THESE FIVE DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES STAND?
>> WOLF, I WOULD BE SURPRISED IF
WE DON'T LEARN MORE FROM THESE
CANDIDATES.
WE'VE HEARD ELIZABETH WARREN UP
TO THIS POINT HAS REALLY
REIGNITED IT CERTAINLY ON THE
CAMPAIGN TRAIL.
HER DECISION TO GO OUT THERE AND
SAY THAT SHE THINKS THAT THE
PRESIDENT SHOULD BE IMPEACHED,
THE HOUSE SHOULD START MOVING
FORWARD WITH IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDINGS, IS GOING TO FORCE
THE OTHER CANDIDATES TO HAVE TO
WEIGH IN ON IT.
NOW, WE'VE HEARD SOME THINGS,
BUT WE REALLY HAVEN'T HEARD
DEFINITIVE ANSWERS UP TOXCXC
POINT, WOLF.
>> VERY INTERESTING, SPEAKING OF
ELIZABETH WARREN, PHIL, THE
SENATOR, SHE'LL BE ON THE STAGE
TONIGHT DURING THE 8:00 P.M. ST.
HER CAMPAIGN HAS JUST UNVEILED A
TRULY SWEEPING PROPOSAL
INVOLVING STUDENT LOAN DEBT, AS
WELL AS FREE TUITION TO ALL
PUBLICGES ACR?
UNITED STATES.
WHAT MORE HAVE YOU LEARNED?
>> YEAH, WOLF, IT'S IN KEEPING
WITH WHAT SENATOR WARREN HAS
BEEN DOING THROUGHOUT THE COURSE
OF HER CAMPAIGN, ROLLING OUT
SWEEPING PROGRESSIVE, FURTHER
REACHING THAN ANY OTHER
CANDIDATE IN THE CAMPAIGN, TYPES
OF PROPOSALS.
THIS ONE SPECIFICALLY WOULDACTU
DEMOCRATS TALKING ABOUT FREE
CO■RE
COLLEGE.
THAT'SNG THAT IS PART
THISOPOSAL.ART OF ING WARREN TA
$1.25 TRILLION ACROSS THE
FORGIVE UP TO 75% OF
THE OUTSTANDING DEBT PROPOSAL I
$1.25 TRILLION, IF YOU'RE
MAKING $100,000 OR LESS, YOU
WOULD BE AVAILABLE TO HAVE
$50,000 IN FORGIVENESS.
IT WOULD MOVE AALE F
SOMETHING WE'VE SEEN REPEATEDLY,
WHETHER IT'S ON HEALTH CARE OR
ON FOREIGN POLICY, NOW ON
STUDENT LOANS, ELIZABETH WARREN
BELIEVES HER LANE IS THE POLICY
LANE.
HER LANE IS IN THE WEEDS POLICY.
SO FAR, THAT HASN'T NECESSARILY
BROUGHT HER TO THE TOP OF THE
POLLS, BUT EVERYTHING YOU'VE
SEEN AND HEARD HER CAMPAIGN
OVER THE COURSE OF THE LAST
COUPLE OF WEEKS, THEY'RE
COMFORTABLE WITH THIS LANE, THEY
BELIEVE AT SOME POINT IT WILL■?.
>> COULD A?RAMATIC PROPOSAL
LIKE THIS?■■■■< NEEDLE FOR7■NAT?
>> I THINK IT'S SOMETHING THAT'S
REALLY GOING TO WORK WELL WITH
THE LIBERAL BASE.
AND WHEN PHIL TALKS ABOUT HER
BEING THE POLICY PRESENCE, SHE
REALLY IS.
SHE'S STEEPED IN POLICY.
SHE COMES FROM BEING A COLLEGE
PROFESSOR, VERY PROFESSORIAL.
SHE'S ALSO VERY FOCUSED, THOUGH,
ON LIBERAL POLICIES.
SO WHEN SHE'S TALKING ABOUT LOAN
FORGIVENESS AND IMPEACHMENT,
THESE ARE ALL ISSUES THAT ARE
GOING TO PLAY TO THAT LEFT SIDE
OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY, WHERE
THERE'S A LOT OF COMPETITION, AS
WE KNOW, FOR RIGHT NOW.
AS PHIL NOTES, NO ONE'S REALLY
BROKEN OUT EXCEPT FOR BERNIE
SANDERS.
BUT THAT MIGHT BE PERHAPS
BECAUSE OF NAME I.D.
BUT HE HAS, OF COURSE, A LOT OF
SUPPORT AND THEY'RE VYING FOR
THE SAME SUPPORTERS.
SO IT WILL BE INTERESTING TO
CONTRAST NOT ONLY BERNIE
SANDERS, ELIZABETH WARREN
TONIGHT, BUT ALSO KAMALA HARRIS
AND PETE BUTTIGIEG AND AMY
KLOBUCHAR, WHO SEEMS TO BE THE
ODD DUCK OUT, BECAUSEHE'S NOT
NECESS??■■■■;■■ REAL;;? OF ■==■=
PRESTON, PHIL MATTINGLY,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AND TO OUR VIEWERS, STAY WITH
CNN FOR TONIGHT'S SPECIAL TOWN
HALL EVENT LIVE FROM NEW
HAMPSHIRE.
WE'LL HEAR FROM FIVE OF THE TOP
DEMOCRATIC CONTENDERS WITHIN AN
EYE ON THE WHITE HOUSE.
IT ALL STARTS RIGHT AFTER T"THE
SITUATION ROOM", 7:00 P.M.
EASTERN.
>>> COMING UP, THE MUELLER
REPORT PAINTS A PICTURE OF AFTER
WHITE HOUSE WHERE TOP OFFICIALS
ROUTINELY IGNORED POTENTIALLY
ILLEGAL ORDERS FROM PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
BUT THE PRESIDENT INSISTS HE
REMAINS IN TOTAL CONTROL OF HIS
ADMINISTRATION.
WE'LL DISCUSS THAT AND ALL THE
LATEST POLITICAL NEWS.
THAT'S JUST AHEAD.
So, you're open all day,
every day.
That's what 24/7 means, sugar.
Kind of like how you
get 24/7 access
to licensed agents with GEICO.
Hmm?
Yeah, you just go online,
or give them a call anytime.
You don't say.
Yep. Now what will it take
to get 24/7 access
to that lemon meringue pie?
PIE!
PIE'S COMING!
That's what it takes, baby.
GEICO®. Great service
from licensed agents, 24/7.
When did you see the sign?
When I needed to create a better
visitor experience.
Improve our workflow.
Attract new customers.
That's when FASTSIGNS
recommended fleet graphics.
Yeah, and now business
is rolling in.
Get started at fastsigns.com.
Hey! It's me! Your dry skin!
I'm craving something we're
missing.
The ceramides in CeraVe.
They help restore my natural
barrier,
so I can lock in moisture.
We've got to have each other's
backs...
CeraVe.
Now the #1 dermatologist
recommended skincare brand.
If you see traces of blood
when you brush or floss,
you don't have to choose
between healthy gums
and strong teeth.
Complete Protection
from parodontax
has 8 designed benefits for
healthy gums and strong teeth.
Complete Protection
from parodontax.
HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN
HIGH SPEED INTERNET WHERE YOU
LIVE? WELL YOU CAN, WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITE INTERNET WHEREU
LIVE. HUGHESNET GEN 5 IS FAST.
YOU'LL GET 25MBPS, PLUS BUILT-IN
WI-FI, AND THERE'S NO HARD DATA
LIMITS. SO, WHEREVER YOU LIVE,
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
EVERYTHING YOU LOVE ONLINE.
CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, STAY
INFORMED, WATCH THE LATEST
VIDEOS, AND HELP YOUR KIDS GET■
■■■ ONE CFOR
SATELLITE INTERNET. ACT NOW TO
SAVE BIG WITH OUR LIMITED TIME
OFFER. GET FREE STANDARD
INSTALLATION BY CALLING RIGHT
NOW. SO, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING
FOR? GET HUGHESNET GEN5. TO
ORDER, CALL THE NUMBER ON YOUR
SCREEN. BE SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR
HOME PHONE SERVICE, TOO. CALL
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN
TODAY.
>>> BREAKING NEWS.
HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE
MEMBERS HAVE JUST SUBPOENAED
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S FORMER WHITE
HOUSE COUNSEL, DON McGAHN.
IT COMES AS HOUSE DEMOCRATS ARE
HUDDLING RIGHT NOW IN AN URGENT
CONFERENCE CALL.
LET'S GET SOME MORE WITH OUR
POLITICAL AND LEGAL EXPERTS,
CHRIS CILLIZZA, DON Mc■@HNNT
30■ ■ ■  TES■ ■ EFp
MUELLEEFORE THE X TEAM.
HOW IMPORTANT WOULD HIS
TESTIMONY BE BEFORHEOUSE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE?
>> WELL, I MEAN, I THINK
IMPORTANT, ONE THING TO YOUR
POINT THAT MITIGATES IT A LITTLE
BIT IS HE SPENT 30 HOURS TALKING
TO THE SPECIAL COUNSEL.
SO PRESUMABLY, MOST OF WHAT HE
KNOWS, MUELLER KNEW AND PUT IN
THE REPORT.
THAT SAID, THERE ARE SEVERAL
INSTANCES ( THAT I WOULD LIKE■
REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS WOULD
LIKE TO HEAR OF THAT
INVOLVE McGAHN.
ONE BEING THAT TRUMP SAYS HE
WANTS McGAHN TO FIRE MUELLER,
AND HE CALLS HIM BACK WHEN "THE
NEW YORK TIMES" BREAKS THE NEWS
AND SAYS, HEY, CAN YOU SAY
THAT'S NOT TRUE?
AND McGAHN SAYS, NO, I WON'T DO
THAT.
TRUMP HAS SAID THAT DIDN'T
HAPPEN.
HE SAID IT AT THE TIME, HE SAID
IT SINCE.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THAT WOULD
BENEFIT FROM FURTHER
EXPLICATION.
PLUS, THIS IS A GUY, DONALD
TRUMP, WE KNOW, WALKED UP, SOME
PEOPLE WOULD SAY BROKE -- BUT
DONALD TRUMP WALKED UP TO THE
LINE A NUMBER OF TIMES, LEGALLY
SPEAKING.
DON McGAHN WAS RIGHT IN THE
CENTER OF THAT AND MIGHT BE ABLE
TO SHED EVEN MORE LIGHT ON WHAT
BOB MUELLER SORT OF SHONE A
LIGHT ON, ALREADY.
>> IT'S ONE THING TO READ HIS
QUOTES IN THE MUELLER REPORT AND
ANOTHER THING TO SEE HIM ON
TELEVISION SAYING THOSE KINDS OF
THINGS, PRESUMABLY INCLUDING
SOME MORE.
THE DEMOCRATS, SUSAN, THEY'RE
RIGHT NOW■■@ App3aT CONFERENCEC
DEMOCRATS.
DO THEY GO FORWARD IMMEDIATELY
WITH IMPEACHMENT OR■■■■■■■■0■■■.
HOW DO YOU SEE IT?
>> I THINK IT'S TROUBLING TO SEE
THEM -- TO NOT BE PREPARED TO AT
LEAST LAUNCH AN IMPEACHMENT
INQUIRY, WHICH IS SEPARATE THAN
ACTUALLY IMPEACHING SOMEONE.
YOU KNOW, THE MUELLER REPORT
HAS -- CONTAINS INFORMATION THAT
IS JUST DEVASTATING.
IT DESCRIBES A PRESIDENT WHO WAS
AWARE OF A FOREIGN CAMPAIGN
CRIMINAL CONSPIRACY TO INTERFERE
ON THE U.S. ELECTION, WHO
WELCOMED THAT HELP, WHO LIED TO
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
IT DESCRIBES A PRESIDENT WHO ON
MULTIPLE OCCASIONS OBSTRUCTED
JUSTICE.
AND WE SHOULD BE CAREFUL TO NOT
MINCE WORDS HERE.
YES, ROBERT MUELLER DID NOT MAKE
THAT ACCUSATION.
BUT IN THE REPORT, HE LAYS OUT
WITH EXCRUCIATING DETAIL HOW
TRUMP'S CONDUCT MET EVERY SINGLE
STATUTORY ELEMENT OF THE CRIME.
HE SAYS, THERE ARE NO
CONSTITUTIONAL OR LEGAL DEFENSES
FOR THIS CONDUCT.
HEP JUST DOESN'T SAY THAT LAST
SENTENCE.
AND THEREFORE THE PRESIDENT --
THE PRESIDENT HAS COMMITTED A
CRIME.
>> IN PART BECAUSE A S ■■■ENT, E
DEPARTMENT, CAN'T BE CHARGED!
>> EXACTLY.
AND HE CLEARLY RELIES ON THIS
OLC PRECEDENT, IN SAYING, I
CAN'T EVEN MAKE THIS ACCUSATION,
BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT CAN'T BE
INDICTED.
SO IF WHAT HAPPENS IS THE
DEMOCRATS RESPOND BY MAKING THIS
A PURELY POLITICAL CALCULATION,
BASICALLY, DO WE HAVE ENOUGH
VOTES TO REMOVE HIM FROM OFFICE,
THAT MEANS THAT UNDER THE OLC
GUIDELINES, THE PRESIDENT CAN'T
BE HELD ACCOUNTABLE THROUGH THE
CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM AND THE
PRESIDENT CAN'T BE HELD
ACCOUNTABLE THROUGH THE
CONGRESSIONAL, CONSTITUTIONAL
MECHANISM.
I THINK THAT HAS REALLY SCARY
IMPLICATIONS.
>> ALSO, JUST ONE QUICK POINT TO
ADD, AS SUSAN SAID, MUELLER
DIDN'T COME OUT AND SAY, DONALD
TRUMP OBSTRUCTED JUSTICE, BUT HE
KIND OF SAYS IT IN THE NEGATIVE
WAY, IN THAT HE SAYS, IF I COULD
EXONERATE HIM, WE ■ ULD.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
WELL, THE LOLUSION IS,
WHAT'S THE OPPOSITE OF ■■■HE SAF
>>■ MUELLER REPORT MAKES
CLEAR THATND THE CURRENTLY
OLC GUIDANCE, THISD OF
INVESTIGATION CAN ONLY EXONERATE
A PRESIDENT.
KIT NOT EVEN ACCUSE HIM.
>> OLC IS THE OFFICE OF LEGAL
COUNSEL AT THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT.
YOU KNOW THAT, WE KNOW THAT,
SOME OF THE VIEWERS MIGHT NOT
KNOW WHAT OLC IS.
SABRINA SIDDIQUI, THE PRESIDENT
SAYS -- SAID IT TODAY, HE'S NOT
EVEN A LITTLE BIT WORRIED ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT.
SHOULD HE BE?
>> WELL, I THINK SO LONG AS
REPUBLICANS ARE IN CONTROL OF
THE SENATE, IT'S HIGHLY UNLIKELY
THAT THE PRESIDENT WILL BE
IMPEACHED.
THAT DOES GO BACK TO SORT OF THE
POLITICAL CALCULATION THAT
DEMOCRATS ARE MAKING, WHERE EVEN
IF HOUSE DEMOCRATS DID MOVE TO
IMPEACH THE PRESIDENT, THERE
WOULD NOT BE SUFFICIENT VOTES IN
THE SENATE TO ACTUALLY REMOVE
HIM FROM OFFICE.
EVEN IF YO LOOK AT THE AFTERMATH
OF THIS REPORT, WHICH IS
INCREDIBLY DAMNING AND REALLY
LAYING BARE THE MANY INSTANCES
IN WHICH THE PRESIDENT AT A
MINIMUM SOUGHT TO OBSTRUCT
JUSTICE, THE SILENCE FROM
REPUBLICANS ON CAPITOL HILL HAS,
AS USUAL, BEEN DEAFENING, YOU
HAD SENATOR MITT ROMNEY COME OUT
AND BE VERY CRITICAL, MORE SO
THAN HIS COLLEAGUES, OF THE ESI
DIDN'T ACTUALLY RECOMMEND ANY
ACTION AGAINST THE PRESIDENT.
AND OTHER REPUBLICANS WHO HAVE
TALKED ABOUT THE REPORT HAVE
ONLY TALKED ABOUT THE NO
COLLUSION ASPECT OF IT.
THEY HAVE ALMOST ENTIRELY
IGNORED THE ALLEGATIONS WITH
RESPECT TO OBSTRUCTION.
ANDS THAT WHY DEMOCRATS WANT TO
BE VERY CAREFUL ABOUT HOW THEY
PURSUE THIS PROCESS, WHEY
DON'T IMMEDIATELY MOVE FROM THE
REDACTED REPORT TO IMPEACHMENT,
BUT THEY SUBPOENA WITNESSES AND
DOCUMENTS, THEY USE THIS REPORT
AS A ROAD MAP.
AND RIALEALLY TRY TO BUILD THE E
BEFORE THE AMERICAN PUBLIC.
>> SAMANTHA VINOGRAD, THE
MUELLER REPORT CLEARLY LAYS OUT
A SERIES OF WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIALS AND OTH■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
THE PRESIDENT'S ■, IN PART
BECAUSE THEY WERE TRYING TO
PROTECT HIM FROM E■■■■■■■■■■■■■.
FT. WAS ASKED■ ABOUT THATER
TODAY BY CNN.
LISTEN TO THIS.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED THAT YOUR
STAFF IS IGNORING YOUR■ ORDERS S
UELLER REPORT PORTRAYS?
■■L■'L■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■  MY ORDER.
>> THAT WA KAITLAN COLLINS
ASKING THAT QUES■dr  ■ ■ ■ HAsaT
>>  IT'S FACTUALLY UNTRUE,
ACCORDING TO THE MUELLER REPORT,
THE WOODWARD BOOK, AND OTHER
REPORTING.
AND WOLF, THIS SOUNDS LIKE
SOMETHING I WOULD EXPECT TO HEAR
ON AN EPISODE OF "GAME OF
THRONES" FROM THE MAD KING OR
QUEEN SCIRCI.
I SPENT A LOT OF HOURS IN THE
SITUATION ROOM WITH PRESIDENT
OBAMA.
AL OF PEOPLE DIRECTLY DISAGREED
WITH HIM WHEN HE HAD IDEAS OR
SUGGESTIONS, INCLUDING HIS LEGAL
ADVISERS, WHO SAID, MR.
PRESIDENT, CONSIDER THE LEGAL
ANGLE OF AN IDEA THAT YOU HAVE.
WHAT WE HAVE HERE IS SOMETHING
VERY DIFFERENT.
WE HAVE STAFF WAGING A SILENT
MUTINY AGAINST PRESIDENT TRUMP,
BECAUSE THEY DO NOT FEEL
COMFORTABLE SHARING THE LEGALITY
OF A MATTER DIRECTLY WITH HIM OR
SAYING HE HAS A BAD IDEA.
THE PRESIDENT SHOULD HAVE A
THAT IMPLEMENTS HIS GUIDANCE,
INCLUDING HIS EXECUTIVE ORDERS,
AND THE UNITED STATES SHOULD
HAVE WHITE HOUSE STAFF THAT'S
NOT WORKING HOURS IN THE DAY,
MANAGING THE PRESIDENT'S WORST
IMPULSES, BUT INSTEAD, THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE TO HAVE
A TEAM THAT'S ALL HANDS ON DECK,
ACTUALLY MANAGING OUR NATIONAL
SECURITY.
>> WELL, IN DISOBEYING HIM, JUST
ONE QUICK THING, IN DISOBEYING
HIM, IT'S PROBABLY THE BEST
THING THAT THEY COULD HAVE DONE
FOR HIM, LEGALLY SPEAKING.
DON McGAHN CARRIES OUT DONALD
TRUMP'S ORDER TO FIRE BOB
MUELLER, WE'RE IN A DIFFERENT
PLACE TODAY THAN WE WERE.
IF REX TILLERSON SAID
REPEATEDLY, HE ASKED ME TO DO
THINGS AND I HAD TO EXPLAIN TO
HIM THEY WERE AGAINST THE LAW.
SO DISOBEYING MY ORDERS CAN MEAN
APPLYING THE LAW, THAT'S SCARY.
>> EVEROUND.
THERE'S MORE NEWS WE'RE
FOLLOWING, INCLUDING BREAKING
NEWS INTO THE INVESTIGATION AS
TO WHO MAY BE RESPONSIBLE FOR
THE DEADLY SUICIDE ATTACKS ON
CHURCHES AND HOTELS.
I don't keep track of regrets.
And I don't add up the years.
But what I do count on...
is BOOST®.
Delicious BOOST®
High Protein Nutritional Drink
has 20 grams of protein,
with 26 essential
vitamins and minerals.
BOOST® High Protein.
Look for savings on BOOST®
in your Sunday paper.
Don't tell your mother.
Dad, it's fine.
We have ALLSTATE.
AND WITH CLAIMRATEGUARD
THEY WON'T RAISE YOUR RATES
JUST BECAUSE OF A CLAIM.
That's why you're my favorite...
I KNOW.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
♪♪
Be right back.
With moderate
to severe Crohn's disease,
I was there, just not
always where I needed to be.
Is she alright?
I hope so.
So I talked to my doctor
about HUMIRA.
I learned HUMIRA is for people
who still have symptoms
of Crohn's disease
after trying other medications.
And the majority
of people on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom relief
and many achieved remission
in as little as 4 weeks.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have
happened; as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Be there for you, and them.
Ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA,
remission is possible.
♪
♪♪
AHHHH!
We're here.
♪♪
>>> BREAKING NEWS.
AUTHORITIES IN THE UNITED STATES
BELIEVE THEY'VE IDENTIFIED A KEY
TERRORIST CON■  T■■ ■@[@■■; BOM
IN HOTELS AND CHURCHES ACROSS
SRI LANKA.■■@■ST FOUR■AMONG THE.
CNN'S WILLp RIPLEY IS JOINING U
THE■4UNT IS ON FOR THE
ATTACKERS.
WILL, GIVE US THE VERY LATEST.
>> Reporter: WELL, WOLF, BARBARA
STARR HAS LEARNED FROM TWO U.S.
OFFICIALS THAT THIS KEY
TERRORIST DOES HAVE CONNECTIONS
TO ISIS AND OTHER INTERNATIONAL
TERROR ORGANIZATIONS.
BUT THE KEY AND UNANSWERED
QUESTION HERE IN SRI LANKA
TONIGHT AND THE REASON WHY
TH■8■8ECURITY AT
HOTELS LIKE THIS ONE, WELL, THEY
JUST DON'T KNOW IF THERE ARE
MORE TERRORISTS OUT THERE.TONIGN
SR AND A RACE TO TRACK
DOWN A TERROR NETWORK BEFORE IT
STRIKES AGAIN.
IN COLOMBO, THE BOMB SQUAD
PERFORMING THIS CONTROLLED
DETONATION OF A SUSPICIOUS VAN
NEAR ST. ANTHONY'S CHURCH, ONE
OF THE SANCTUARIES TARGETED IN
EASTER SUNDAY THAT KILLED AT
LEAST ■E AND INJURED
HUNDREDS MORE.
THIS NEW VIDEO■@■@HOWS MAN STAT@
TV CALLS A SN THE ST.
SEBASTIAN'S CHURCH BOMBING.
CHURCH OFFICIALS SAY A BOMB IN
HIS BACKPACK, ONE OF SIX
HOTE?,
HOTELS JUST BEFORE A SERIES OF
EIGHT EXPLOSIONS ROCKED THIS
SOUTH ASIAN ISLAND NATION.
U.S. AND I INTELLIGENCEAGENCIES
ISLAMIST GROUP WAS PLOTTING AN
ATTACK.
THE GOVERNMENT APOLOGIZING FOR
THVE GOVERNMENT FAILURE,
PROMISING TO COMPENSATE VICTIMS'
FAMILIES.
>> THEY JUST ATTACK FROM
EVERYONE.
AND IT JUST DOESN'T ANY
■4d4■p48rç■ç■■■Yy8>■>(■>■=p÷p÷p
ASSISTING, AS INVESTIGATORS
UNCOVER EVIDENCE OF WHAT COULD
BE A MUCH LARGE TERROR PLOT.
POLICE FOUND 87 DETONATORS AT A
COLOMBO BUS STATION.
THEY DIFFUSED A 6-FOOT PIPE BOMB
ON THE MAIN ROAD NEAR THE
AIRPORT.
SO FAR, AT LEAST 24 PEOPLE ARE
UNDER ARREST IN CONNECTION WITH
THE BOMBINGS.
A U.S. OFFICIAL TELLS CNN THE
ATTACKS ARE ISIS-INSPIRED.
ZBLF A BIG NOISE AND BROKEN
GLASSES AND DUST AND ALL THE
PEOPLE ARE SHOUTING, WEEPING.
AND WE CAN'T REALIZE WHAT
HAPPENED.
>> Reporter: BOMB AFTER BOMB,
CITY AFTER CITY, IT WAS A
TERRIFYING EASTER SUNDAY ACROSS
SRI LANKA.
THE PRIMARY TARGETS, FOUR HOTELS
FULL OF FOREIGNERS AND THREE
CHURCHES FULL OF CHRISTIANS.
ONE BLAST ROCKED ST. SEBASTIAN'S
CHURCH AT THE END OF EASTER
MASS.
THE HORROR.WRS RAN F
LIFELESS BODIES, BLOODSTAINED
PEWS, DEBRIS AND HUMAN REMAINS
PROPELLED THROUGH THE SANCTUARY
INTO THE STREETS.
>> THERE WERE CHILDREN, THERE
WERE WOMEN AND ALL CLOSE BY, AND
ALL WERE BLOWN OFF ALMOST.
SO WE HAVE MORE THAN 10■O■g■g
O WERE KILLED ON THE SPOT.
>> Reporter: THE VIOLENCE
REMINISCENT OF SRI LANKA'S
BLOODY 26-YEAR CIVIL WAR.
THE FIGHTING ENDED TEN YEARS AGO
NEXT MONTH.
TONIGHT, A NEW THREAT PUTTING
THIS ENTIRE NATION ON LOCKDOWN.
NORMALLY BUSY STREETS EMPTY, A■;
NATIONWIDE CURFEW IN EFFECT.
AND GROWING FEARS AN
INTERNATIONAL TERROR GROUP MAY
BE SILENTLY PLOTTING ITS NEXT
MOVE.
>> Reporter: WOLF, ALL THREE OF
THE HOTELS THAT WERE BOMBED ARE
JUST A VERY SHORT DISTANCE FROM
WHERE I'M STANDING RIGHT NOW.
AND THE HOTELS THAT WERE NOT HIT
HAVE SECURITY AT THE PERIMETERS
TO MAKE SURE=, THAT IF THERE ISN
ATTEMPTED ATTACK, THEY WON'T BE
ABLE TO GET IN, BUT THAT IS
DOING LITTLE TO SOOTHE THE
NERVES OF A LOT OF NERVOUS
PEOPLE, ESPECIALLY FOREIGN
TOURISTS WHO HAVE BEEN TRYING TO
GET OUT OF THIS CITY.
WOLF?
>> JUST BE CAREFUL OVER THERE.
g■2■■■■LEY ON THE SCENE FOR US.
WE'LL GET BACK TO YOU.
THANK YOU VERY, VERY MUCH.
COMING UP, A SURPRISING TWIST IN
THE WAKE OF A DARING RAID ON ONE
OFOREA'S EMBASSIES.
My experience with USAA
has been excellent.
They really appreciate
the military family
and it really shows.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
It was funny because
when we would call
another insurance company,
hey would say
“Oh we can't beat USAA”
We're the Webber family.
We're the Tenney's
We're the Hayles,
and we're USAA members for life.
♪
Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
♪
So in this commercial we see
two travelers
at a Comfort INN with a glow
around them,
so people watching will be like,
"Wow, maybe I'll glow too
if I book direct at
ChoiceHotels.com."
Who glows?
Just say, Badda Book.
Badda Boom.
Book now at ChoiceHotels.com.
Who knew. - Yeah.
So you're with The UPS Store?
Yes. In fact, we printed
these right here.
Oh, I thought you guys
just did shipping.
No we do printing,
packing, faxing,
notarizing, shredding,
mailboxing,
copying, taping, binding,
Uh huh...
consulting, designing,
returning,
storing, and freighting.
Oh, and of course, shipping.
So you're into shipping?
We also do printing,
packing, faxing...
Come in to The UPS Store today
for every ING your small
business needs.
And of course, shipping.
Hi I'm
>>> TONIGHT WE'RE FOLLOWING
SURPRISING NEW DEVELOPMENTS IN
THE WAKE OF THIS YEAR'S
MYSTERIOUS BREAK IN AT A NORTH
KOREAN
CNN'S B TODD HAS B
WORKING HIS SOURCES.
BRIAN, THERE'S BEEN A RAID AND
AN ARREST BOTH HERE IN THE
UNITED STATES?
>> THAT'S RIGHT, WOLF.
WE HAVE N INFORMATION TONIGHT
ON THE EXTRAORDINARY PRESSURE
BEING PLACED ON MEMBERS OF THE
GROUP WHICH CONDUCTED THAT RAID
AT NORTH KOREA'S EMBASSY IN
MADRID, SPAIN.
ONE  MEN IS NOW IN
HIDING IN FEAR FOR HIS LIFE.
'RE TOLD THAT THE INFORMATION
THESE MEN LIKELY GOT FROM THAT
EMBASSY COULD BE VERY VALUABLE
TO WESTERN INTELLIGENCE.
>>> IT WAS A BIZARRE AND BRAZEN
HEIST AIMED AT■■■■
ITS DICTATOR KIM JONG-UN.
CARRIED OUT IN BROAD DAYLIGHT
AGAINST THEw■TALw■w■w■w■w■w■w■I■
EMBASSY IN SPAIN BACK IN
FEBRUARY.
TEN MEN GAINED ENTRY INT
COMPOUND ALLEGEDLY AS POSING AS
BUSINESSMEN, TYING UP THE STAFF
AND BEATING THEM.
SPANISH OFFICIALS SAY BEFORE
MAKING OFF IN EMBASSY VEHICLES
WITH A STASH OF THUMB DRIVES,
HARD DRIVES, COMPUTERS AND
PHONES.
A GOLD MINE, SPIES SAY, FOR
WESTERN INTELLIGENCE.
>> POLICE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT CNN LEARNED
U.S. MARSHALS ARE SEARCHING FOR
THIS MAN, A MEXICAN NATIONAL AND
U.S. RESIDENT WHO SPANISH
AUTHORITIES SAY LED THE EMBASSY
ASSAULT.
AUTHORITIES RAIDED HONG'S
APARTMENT THURSDAY BUT DIDN'T
FIND HIM THERE.
A SOURCE CLOSE TO HONG SHARED
THIS VIDEO EXCLUSIVELY WITH CNN.
TONIGHT HIS LAWYER TELLS CNN
ADRIAN HONG HAS GONNA GROUND.
>> HE CERTAINLY FEARS FOR HIS
SAFETY.
WE DO HAVE REASON TO BELIEVE
THAT NORTH KOREAN HIT SQUADS
HAVE BEEN DISPATCHED TO TARGET
MR. HONG.
>> Reporter: ADRIAN HONG IS A
LEAD EFFORT OF THE GROUP ONCE
KNOWN AS CHILE MASS CIVIL
DEFENSE.
>> IT IS A BRUTAL TOTALITARIAN
REGIME.
>> Reporter: THEY WANT TO BE
CALLED THE LIBERAL GOVERNMENT
MUCH FREE GISAN, A SWORN ENEMY
OF KIM'S REGIME.
>> THE GOAL IS TO OVERTHROW THE
REGIME AND BRING HUMAN RIGHTS
AND OTHER FREEDOMS TO NORTH
KOREA.
>> Reporter: A FORMER NORTH
KOREAN AN ALLEGED MEMBER OF THE
GROUP WAS TAKEN INTO CUSTODY BY
U.S. MARSHALS IN LOS ANGELES ON
THURSDAY, THOUGH IT IS NOT CLEAR
WHAT HE HAS BEEN CHARGED WITH.
HIS CASE IS UNDER SEAL AND HIS
LAWYER HASN'T COMMENTED.
THIS IS A PICTURE OF AHN TAKEN
WITH THE SON OF KIM JONG-UN'S
HALF BROTHER.
ACCORDING TO ADRIAN HONG'S
LAWYER, CHRISTOFFER AHN HELPED
EXTRACT THAT YOUNG MAN AND HIS
FAMILY FROM MACAU TO A SAFE
LOCATION TWO YEARS AGO.
SHORTLY AFTER KIM ALLEGEDLY HAD
HIS HALF BROTHER MURDERED AT AN
AIRPORT IN MALAYSIA.
IT'S NOT CLEAR IF AHN WAS
INVOLVED IN THE RAID ON THE
EMBASSY IN SPAIN ON FEBRUARY
22nd.
HONG'S LAWYER ADMITS HIS CLIENT
WAS.
HE SAYS THE GROUP WAS INVITED
INSIDE AND WASN'T VIOLENT.
SPANISH OFFICIALS SAY ADRIAN
HONG CAUGHT A PLANE TO THE U.S.
SHORTLY AFTER THE EMBASSY RAID
AND HONG'S GROUP SAYS IT SHARED
THE MATERIAL TAKEN FROM THE RAID
WITH THE FBI AT THE FBI'S
REQUEST.
WHAT COULD THE BUREAU LEARN
ABOUT OPERATIONS AT THAT NORTH
KOREAN EMBASSY?
>> THE NORTH KOREANS, WE
SUSPECT, ARE INVOLVED IN
NARCOTICS, IN MURDER, ALL SORTS
OF THINGS, AND GET CONFIRMATION
OF THIS HARD INTELLIGENCE IS
VERY DIFFICULT TO DO AND YOU
NEVER GET AN OPPORTUNITY LIKE
THIS.
>> Reporter: ADRIAN HONG'S
ATTORNEY TELLS US HE IS
CONCERNED THAT IF HIS CLIENT IS
TAKEN INTO CUSTODY, HE MIGHT
EVENTUALLY BE EXTRADITED TO
NORTH KOREA.
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT WHILE NOT
COMMENTING ON ANY OTHER ASPECT
OF THIS CASE HAS TOLD CNN THAT
ESSENTIALLY IT WOULD NOT TRY TO
FACILITATE THAT EXTRADITION.
THE FBI, WHEN WE ASKED ABOUT ANY
INFORMATION THAT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
SHARED WITH THE BUREAU FROM THAT
RAID AT NORTH KOREA'S EMBASSY IN
MADRID WOULD NOT COMMENT ON ANY
OF THIS.
WOLF?
>> WHAT A STORY THIS IS.
BRIAN TODD, THANKS VERY MUCH.
COMING UP WE'LL HAVE MORE ON
THIS HOUR'S BREAKING NEWS.
THE HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE
JUST SUBPOENAED PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S FORMER WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL DON McGAHN.
IF HE TESTIFIES, WILL IT LEAD
CONGRESS CLOSER TO IMPEACHING
THE PRESIDENT?
If you see traces of blood
when you brush or floss,
you don't have to choose
between healthy gums
and strong teeth.
Complete Protection
from parodontax
has 8 designed benefits for
healthy gums and strong teeth.
Complete Protection
from parodontax.
Travel and dining
just go together.
Now KAYAK and OpenTable
let you earn travel rewards
every time you dine.
Earn points with each restaurant
reservation on OpenTable
and redeem them for
hotel discounts on KAYAK.
Get started at
KAYAK.com/diningrewards.
Drivers just wont put their
phones down.
We need a solution.
Introducing... Smartdogs.
The first dogs trained to train
humans.
Stopping drivers from: Liking.
Selfie-ing.
And whatever this is.
Available to the public...
never.
Smartdogs are not the answer.
But GEICO has a simple tip.
Turn on "Do Not Disturb While
Driving" mode.
Brought to you by GEICO.
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
So why accept it
from your allergy pills?
Most pills don't finish the job
because they don't
relieve nasal congestion.
Flonase Allergy Relief
is different.
Flonase relieves sneezing,
itchy, watery eyes
and a runny nose, plus nasal
congestion, which pills don't.
Flonase helps block
6 key inflammatory substances.
Most pills only block one.
And 6 is greater than 1.
Start your day
with Flonase
for more complete
allergy relief.
Flonase.
This changes everything.
BEHR presents: Outdone Yourself.
Staining be done...
and stay done through
every season.
BEHR SEMI-TRANSPARENT STAIN.
Find it exclusively
at The Home Depot.
Hey! It's me! Your dry skin!
I'm craving something we're
missing.
The ceramides in CeraVe.
They help restore my natural
barrier,
so I can lock in moisture.
We've got to have each other's
backs...
CeraVe.
Now the #1 dermatologist
recommended skincare brand.
If your moderate to severe
ulcerative colitis
or Crohn's symptoms...
are holding you back...
and your
current treatment
hasn't worked
well enough...
it may be
time for a change.
Ask your doctor
about ENTYVIO®,
the only biologic
developed and approved
just for UC and Crohn's.
ENTYVIO® works at the
site of inflammation
in the GI tract,
and is clinically proven
to help many patients
achieve both symptom
relief and remission.
can happen during
or after treatment.
ENTYVIO® may
increase risk of infection,
PML, a rare, serious,
potentially fatal
brain infection
caused by a virus
may be possible.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection,
experience frequent
infections
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
r problems?■■■@?■ ENTYVIO®.
If your UC orohn's t
isn't working for you,
ask your gastroenterologist
about ENTYVIO®.
ENTYVIO®.
Relief and Remission
within reach.
>>> HAPPENING NOW, BREAKING