ENTYVIO® may
increase risk of infection,
which ca.
PML, a rare, serious,
potentially fatal
brain infection
caused by a virus
may be possible.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection,
experience frequent
infections
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
ver problems  occu?■NTYVIO®.
experience frequent
infections
If your UC or
Crohn's ent
isn't working for you,
ask your gastroenterologist
about ENTYVIO®.
ENTYVIO®.
Relief and Remission
within reach.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
WELCOME BACK TO MANCHESTER, NEW
HAMPSHIRE.
THIS IS CNN'S SPECIAL DEMOCRATIC
TOWN HALL EVENT.
I'M CHRIS CUOMO.
THIS IS A REALLY INTERESTING
NIGHT.
AS YOU HAVE ALREADY SEEN WE'RE
DOING TOWN HALLS WITH FIVE OF
THE TOPOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES.
THE POTENTIAL QUEHH
INCLUDE COLLEGE STUDENTS AND
YOUNG ADULTS REPRESENTING MORE
THAN 30 STATES NATIONWIDE.
TO DO THIS CNN PARTNERED WITH
HARVARD UNIVERSITY'S INSTITUTE
OF POLITICS AND THE NEW
HAMPSHIRE INSTITUTE OF POLITICS.
ALREADY TONIGHT WE HEARD FROM
SENATORS AMY KLOBACHAR AND
ELIZABETH WARREN AND RIGHT NOW
IS SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS OF
VERMONT LEADING THE FIELD AMONG
THE HARVARD INSTITUTE OF
POLITICS.
PLEASE WELCOME SENATOR SANDERS.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> YOU TOO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
HOW ABOUT OUR FIRST QUESTION.
>> WHY NOT?
>> WHY NOT, INDEED.
>> WHAT ELSE DO WE HAVE TO DO?
>> WE'LL TALK LATER.
>> HE'S FROM MASSACHUSETTS AND A
JUNIOR AT THE UNIVERSITY OF
MASSACHUSETTS, LOWELL.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
>> HI, SENATOR.
>> HI.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> YOU REDUCED YOUR MEDICARE FOR
ALL LEGISLATION PACKAGE, MANY OF
THEM ARE RUNNING ALONG SIDE OF
YOU FOR PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES.
IN THIS LEGISLATION YOU CALLED
FOR AN END TO PRIVATE HEALTH
INSURANCE COMPANIES.
HOW DO YOU PLAN TO PHASE OUT
THESE COMPANIES FOR YOUR NEW
MEDICARE FOR ALL INSURANCE.
>> EXCELLENT QUESTION ON A ISSUE
THAT MILLIONS OF AMERICANS STAY
UP NIGHTS ABOUT.
WE HAVE A DYSFUNCTIONAL HEALTH
CARE SYSTEM IN WHICH 30 MILLION
AMERICANS HAVE NO HEALTH
INSURANCE AT ALL.
EVEN MORE ARE UNDERINSURED WITH
HIGH DEDUCTIBLES AND
CO-PAYMENTS.
WE BABPAY BY FAR THE HIGHEST PRS
IN THE WORLD.
IN TERMS OF INFANT MORTALITY AND
LIFE EXPECTANCY NOT MAPARTICULAY
GOOD.
AND FOR ALL OF THAT WE SPEND
TWICE AS MUCH PER CAPITA AS ANY
COUNTRY ON EARTH.
THE FUNCTION OF THE CURRENT
HEALTH CARE SYSTEM IS NOT TO
PROVIDE QUALITY CARE FOR ALL IN
A COST EFFECTIVE WAY.
THE FUNCTION OF THE CURRENT
SYSTEM IS TO MAKE BILLIONS OF
DOLLARS IN PROFITS FOR THE
INSURANCE COMPANIES AND THE DRUG
COMPANIES.
THAT IS THE FUNCTION OF THE
CURRENT SYSTEM AND WHAT I
BELIEVE IS THAT OVER FOUR YEAR
OD■ IS WHAT MY
LEGISLATION IS ABOUT, WE'RE
GOING TO TRANSFORM OUR HEALTH
CARE SYSTEM.
SO FIRST YEAR WE GO FROM 65
YEARS OF AGE TO ELIGIBILITY TO
MEDICARE DOWN TO 55 AND WE COVER
ALL OF THE KIDS IN THE COUNTRY
AND BY THE WAY, DESPITE WHAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS WE EXPAND
BENEFITS FOR SENIOR CITIZENS.
MEDICARE IS A VERY GOOD PROGRAM
BUT IT DOESN'T COVER DENTAL
CARE.
IT DOESN'T COVER EYEGLASSES AND
IT DOESN'T COVER HEARING AIDS
AND WE DO THAT.
BOTTOM LINE IS I BELIEVE FROM
THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART THAT
HEALTH CARE IS A HUMAN RIGHT AND
NOT A PRIVILEGE AND THE BEST WAY
TO GO FORWARD IN MY VIEW IS
THROUGH MEDICARE FOR ALL SINGLE
PAYER PROGRAM.
>> NEXT QUESTION, ANN, JUNIOR AT
HARVARD.
>> SENATOR SANDERS, YOU SAID
THAT YOU BELIEVE THAT PEOPLE
WITH FELONY RECORDS SHOULD BE
ALLOWED TO VOTE WHILE IN PRISON.
DOES THIS MEAN YOU WOULD SUPPORT
INFRANCHISING PEOPLE LIKE THE
BOSTON MARATHON BOMBER, A
CONVICTED TERRORIST AND MURDER?
DO YOU THINK THAT THOSE
CONVICTED OF SEXUAL ASSAULT
SHOULD HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY TO
VOTE FOR POLITICIANS THAT COULD
HAVE A DIRECT IMPACT ON WOMEN'S
RIGHTS?
>> THANK YOU FOR THE QUESTION.
WHAT OUR CAMPAIGN IS ABOUT IS
CREATING A VIBRANT DEMOCRACY.
TODAY AS YOU KNOW WE HAVE ONE OF
THE LOWEST VOTER TURN OUTS OF MY
COUNTRY ON EARTH.
I WANT TO SEE ONE OF THE HIGHEST
VOTER TURN OUTS.
WE'RE SEEING MORE YOUNG PEOPLE
GETTING INVOLVED IN THE
POLITICAL PROCESS BUT NOT
ENOUGH.
AND IN MY VIEW IF YOUNG PEOPLE
VOTED AT THE SAME PERCENTAGE
THAT OLDER PEOPLE VOTED IN THIS
COUNTRY WE WOULD TRANSFORM THIS
NATION.
BUT TO GET TO YOUR POINT, WE
LIVE IN A MOMENT WHERE COWARDLY
REPUBLICAN VOTE GOVERNORS ARE
TRYING TO SUPPRESS THE VOTE.
RIGHT HERE IN NEW HAMPSHIRE
THEY'RE WORKING HARD TO MAKE IT
MORE DIFFICULT FOR YOUNG PEOPLE
TO VOTE AND TO ME THAT IS
INCREDIBLY UNDEMOCRATIC,
UN-AMERICAN PROCESS AND I SAY TO
THOSE PEOPLE, BY THE WAY, IF YOU
DON'T HAVE THE GUTS TO
PARTICIPATE IN FREE AND FAIR
ELECTIONS YOU SHOULD GET ANOTHER
JOB AND GET OUT OF POLITICS.
ALL RIGHT?
SO.
>> SO TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTION,
AS IT HAPPENS IN MY OWN STATE OF
VERMONT FROM THE VERY FIRST DAYS
OF OUR STATE'S HISTORY OUR
CONSTITUTION SAYS EVERYBODY CAN
VOTE.
SO PEOPLE IN JAIL CAN VOTE.
IF SOMEBODY COMMITS A SERIOUS
CRIME, SEXUAL ASSAULT, MURDER,
THEY'RE GOING TO BE PUNISHED.
THEY MAY BE IN JAIL FOR 10
YEARS, 20 YEARS, 50 YEARS, THEIR
WHOLE LIFE.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
COMMIT A SERIOUS CRIME BUT I
THINK THE RIGHT TO VOTE IS
INHERENT TO OUR DEMOCRACY.
YES, EVEN FOR TERRIBLE PEOPLE
BECAUSE ONCE YOU START CHIPPING
AWAY AND YOU SAY WELL THAT GUY
COMMITTED A TERRIBLE CRIME, NOT
GOING TO LET HIM VOTE.
WELL THAT PERSON DID THAT.
NOT GOING TO LET THAT PERSON
VOTE, YOU'RE RUNNING DOWN A
SLIPPERY SLOPE.
SO I BELIEVE PEOPLE COMMIT
CRIMES AND THEY PAID THE PRICE
AND THEY HAVE THE RIGHT TO VOTE.
I BELIEVE EVEN IF THEY'RE IN
JAIL THEY'RE PAYING THEIR PRICE
TO SOCIETY BUT THAT SHOULD NOT
TAKE AWAY THEIR AMERICAN RIGHT
TO PARTICIPATE IN OUR DEMOCRACY.
>> YOU THINK THE BOSTON MARATHON
BOMBER SHOULD VOTE NOT AFTER HE
PAYS HIS DEBT TO SOCIETY BUT
WHILE HE'S IN JAIL.
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
>> I THINK I HAVE WRITTEN MANY
30 SECOND OPPOSITION ADS
THROUGHOUT MY LIFE.
THIS WILL BE JUST ANOTHER ONE.
BUT I DO BELIEVE -- THIS IS WHAT
I BELIEVE.
YOU BELIEVE IN DEMOCRACY?
THAT EVERY SINGLE AMERICAN 18
YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER WHO IS AN
AMERICAN CITIZEN HAS THE RIGHT
TO VOTE?
ONCE YOU START CHIPPING AWAY AT
THAT -- THAT'S WHAT OUR
REPUBLICAN GOVERNORS ARE DOING.
COMING UP WITH ALL KINDS OF
EXCUSES WHILE PEOPLE OF COLOR,
YOUNG PEOPLE, POOR PEOPLE CAN'T
VOTE AND I WILL DO EVERYTHING I
CAN TO RESIST IT.
THIS IS A DEMOCRACY THIS IS A
DEMOCRACY AND WE HAVE TO EXPAND
THAT DEMOCRACY AND EVERY PERSON
HAS A RIGHT TO VOTE.
>> SHE IS A GRADUATE STUDENT
STUDYING JOURNALISM.
SHE'S HERE FROM GEORGIA.
>> YOUR VIEWS ON REPARATIONS
SURPRISED ME ESPECIALLY SINCE
ONE OF THE MESSAGES OF YOUR
CAMPAIGN IS CLOSING THE WEALTH
GAP.
FOR BLACK PEOPLE IT STEMS FROM
THE AFTERMATH OF SLAVERY.
IF IT'S NOT PART OF YOUR PLAN TO
END THE WEALTH GAP FOR BLACK
PEOPLE, WHAT IS?
>> WHAT I HAVE SAID IS THERE IS
LEGISLATION IN THE HOUSE.
AND I HAVE SAID IF THE HOUSE AND
THE SENATE PASS IT I WILL SIGN
IT AND THAT WILL CALL FOR A
STUDY OF THE IMPLICATIONS OF
REPARATIONS AND I THINK WHAT
KENYA IS SAYING IS WHAT WE ALL
KNOW TO BE TRUE.
TODAY IN AMERICA IN THE MIDST OF
MASSIVE INCOME DISPARITY WE HAVE
ANOTHER DISPARITY BETWEEN BLACK
AND WHITE.
AFRICAN AMERICAN FAMILIES HAVE
ONE TENTH THE WEALTH THAT WHITE
FAMILIES HAVE AND THAT IS
UNACCEPTABLE AND WE HAVE TO DEAL
WITH IT.
NOW THE WAY I THINK WE CAN MOST
EFFECTIVELY DEAL WITH THAT AND
THIS IS AN IDEA -- I DIDN'T COME
UP WITH IT.
A CONGRESSMAN FROM SOUTH
CAROLINA, HE CALLED IT THE
10-20-30 LEGISLATION WHICH MEANS
THAT YOU USE 10% OF FEDERAL
FUNDS.
THAT IS A LOT OF MONEY TO FOCUS
ON COMMUNITIES ALL OVER THE
COUNTRY, MINORITY KMCOMMUNITIES
WHO HAVE LONG-TERM POVERTY AND
WE FOCUS ON THOSE COMMUNITIES.
WE MAKE SURE THAT ALL OF THE
KIDS GET THE EDUCATION THAT THEY
NEED.
THEY GET THE HEALTH CARE THAT
THEY NEED.
WE IMPROVE THE INFRASTRUCTURE.
WE IMPROVE BROADBAND.
WE CREATE A SITUATION IN THESE
DISTRESSED COMMUNITIES WHERE WE
TAKE PEOPLE OUT OF POVERTY ALL
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
THAT'S THE DIRECTION I THINK WE
SHOULD GO.
>> NEXT QUESTION.
JORDAN COOK, SOPHOMORE STUDYING
POLITICS AND HISTORY HERE.
HE IS FROM MAINE.
JORDAN, WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION.
>> HELLO SENATOR SANDERS.
WE LIVE IN THE AGE OF
GLOBALIZATION.
INTERNATIONAL TRADE HAS BECOME
INCREASINGLY NECESSARY FOR A
NATION TO REMAIN PROSPEROUS.
TRUMP IN RECENT YEARS LIMITED R
IN AFRICA AND LATIN AMERICA
WHICH HAS GIVEN THE RUSSIANS AND
CHINESE A CHANCE TO INFLUENCE
SUCH REGIONS.
WHAT WILL YOUR TRADE POLICY BE
IN SUCH REGIONS COMPARED TO
TRUMP?
>> GOOD QUESTION.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE LIVE IN A GLOBAL ECONOMY.
I THINK ALL OF US UNDERSTAND THE
IMPORTANCE OF TRADE, BUT I
HAPPEN TO BELIEVE IN FAIR TRADE.
NOT FREE TRADE.
BECAUSE IN THE CONTEXT OF YOUR
QUESTION, YOU HAVE TO APPRECIATE
THAT DISASTROUS TRADE AGREEMENTS
LIKE NAFTA, PERM NANENT NORMAL
TRADE RELATIONS WITH CHINA AND
OTHERS RESULTED IN MILLIONS OF
AMERICANS, HARD WORKING PEOPLE
WHO HAVE LOST THEIR JOBS BECAUSE
PROFITABLE CORPORATIONS IN THIS
COUNTRY SHUTDOWN BECAUSE THEY
WEREN'T MAKING ENOUGH MONEY AND
THEY THOUGHT THEY COULD MAKE
MORE MONEY GOING ABROAD PAYING
PEOPLE $1 AN HOUR OR $2 AN HOUR.
SO I BELIEVE IN TRADE BUT IT HAS
TO BE A TRADE POLICY THAT WORKS
FOR WORKING PEOPLE AND NOT JUST
THE CEOs OF LARGE CORPORATIONS
AND YOUR POINT IS ALSO RIGHT.
WE'RE SEEING CHINA MOVE
AGGRESSIVELY IN LATIN AMERICA
AND AFRICA AND ASIA AND THIS IS
AN ISSUE WE HAVE TO DEAL WITH AS
WELL.
BUT BOTTOM LINE IS TRADE IS A
GOOD THING BUT THERE'S A REASON
WHY MILLIONS OF AMERICANS HAVE
SEEN A DECLINE IN THEIR STANDARD
OF LIVING.
THEY ONCE HAD DECENT PAYING
JOBS.
THOSE JOBS WERE SHIFTED ABROAD
AND THAT'S SOMETHING THAT I
DISAGREE WITH STRONGLY.
>> SENATOR SANDERS, YOU RECENTLY
RELEASED 10 YEARS OF YOUR TAX
RETURNS.
>> I DID.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THAT TOPIC.
ELLEN IS A FRESHMAN AT HARVARD
AND GREW UP IN MASSACHUSETTS.
WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION FOR THE
SENATOR.
>> SENATOR SANDERS, THANK YOU
FOR BEING HERE.
YOUR TAX RETURNS RECENTLY
REVEALED THAT YOU ARE, IN FACT,
A MILLIONAIRE.
HOW WOULD YOU RESPOND TO
CONCERNS THAT YOUR FINANCIAL
STATUS UNDERMINES YOUR AUTHORITY
AS SOMEONE WHO HAS RAILED
AGAINST MILLIONAIRES AND
BILLIONAIRES?
>> THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
AND HERE IT IS.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU READY TO HAVE ME PLEAD
GUILTY.
I PLEAD GUILTY TO HAVE WRITTEN A
BOOK WHICH WAS AN INTERNATIONAL
BEST SELLER.
OKAY?
AND WHEN YOU WRITE A BOOK THAT
MAKES IT TO THE TOP OF THE NEW
YORK TIMES BEST SELLER LIST, YOU
MAKE MONEY.
AND I MADE MONEY.
I SUSPECT THAT IN A COUPLE OF
YEARS MY SALARY WILL GO BACK TO
173,000 WHICH IS WHAT A MEMBER
OF CONGRESS GETS.
BUT I THINK YOUR QUESTION SHOULD
ASK, WELL, NOW THAT YOU WROTE A
BOOK AND YOU MADE MONEY, IS THAT
GOING TO MEAN THAT YOU CHANGE
YOUR POLICIES?
WELL, YOU'RE LOOKING AT SOMEBODY
WHO NOT ONLY VOTED AGAINST
TRUMP'S DISASTROUS TAX PLAN, 83%
OF THE BENEFITS GOING TO THE TOP
1%.
BUT I HAVE AND WILL CONTINUE IN
THIS CAMPAIGN TO FIGHT FOR
PROGRESSIVE TAXATION.
IN OTHER WORDS, WHETHER IT'S
BERNIE SANDERS OR YOUR FAMILY OR
ANYBODY ELSE IN AMERICA WHEN WE
HAVE SO MUCH INCOME AND WEALTH
INEQUALITY.
WHEN THE PEOPLE ON TOP ARE DOING
PHENOMENALLY WELL, YEAH, IF YOU
ARE DOING VERY, VERY WELL IN OUR
ECONOMY YOU SHOULD BE PAYING
YOUR FAIR SHARE OF TAXES.
WE WILL RAISE THOSE TAXES FOR
THE UPPER INCOME PEOPLE.
WE WILL DO AWAY WITH THE TAX
LOOPHOLES AND THE TAX BREAKS
THAT LARGE PRIVATE CORPORATIONS
CURRENTLY RECEIVE.
DO YOU HAPPEN TO KNOW -- ANYBODY
HERE HAPPEN TO KNOW HOW MUCH
AMAZON PAID IN TAXES LAST YEAR?
ZERO.
OWNED BY THE WEALTHIEST GUY IN
AMERICA.
THAT'S AN ABSURD TAX SYSTEM AND
IF ELECTED PRESIDENT I'LL CHANGE
IT.
>> TWO QUICK FOLLOW UPS.
YOU SAID YOU EXPECT YOUR SALARY
TO GO BACK DOWN.
>> UNLESS I WRITE ANOTHER BEST
SELLER.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> OR, WHO MAKES MORE THAN THAT?
WHAT DOES THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES MAKE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> 400.
ARE YOU SAYING THAT YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO WIN?
>> NO.
I'M NOT SAYING THAT.
I'M JUST SAYING THAT I DON'T
THINK ANYBODY BELIEVES THAT
BECAUSE I WROTE A BEST SELLER
THAT I CHANGE MY VIEWS AND
YOU'LL NOW HEAR ME SAY MAYBE WE
OUGHT TO GIVE TAX BREAKS TO
MILLIONAIRES.
>> SO YOU MADE A LOT MORE MONEY
THAN YOU DID THE YEAR BEFORE
BECAUSE OF THE BOOK.
CHARITABLE DONATIONS WHEN WE
LOOK AT YOUR TAXES WENT UP BUT
THEY DIDN'T GO UP
PROPORTIONALLY.
I'M NOT COMING AFTER YOU ABOUT
WHAT YOU GAVE IN YOUR DONATIONS.
MY QUESTION IS THIS, HAVING THE
EXPERIENCE OF HAVING MORE MONEY
AND DECIDING WHAT YOU WANTED TO
DO WITH IT, DID IT GIVE YOU MORE
PERSPECTIVE ABOUT HOW PEOPLE
WITH MORE MONEY FEEL ABOUT THE
GOVERNMENT OR SOMEBODY LIKE YOU
FORCING POLICIES THAT DEMAND
THEM TO GIVE AMOUNTS AS OPPOSED
TO WHAT THEY WANT TO GIVE?
>> AS A MATTER OF FACT IF YOU
READ THE TAX RETURNS, WE WERE
NOT AGGRESSIVE.
WE DIDN'T GO TO ACCOUNTANTS AND
FIGURE OUT HOW WE CAN POSSIBLY
PAY THE LOWEST AMOUNT IN TAXES.
PROBABLY PAID MORE THAN WE
SHOULD HAVE.
YOU RAISE AN INTERESTING
QUESTION.
I GREW UP IN A FAMILY THAT WAS A
WORKING GLASS FAMILY.
I LIVED IN A RENT CONTROLLED
APARTMENT IN NEW YORK.
I KNEW WHAT PAYCHECK TO PAYCHECK
LIFE WAS ABOUT.
I KNEW WHAT TENSION WAS ABOUT IN
A FAMILY.
I'LL TELL YOU THE DIFFERENCE
NOW.
WHEN I WAS A KID MY FAMILY HAD
TO WORRY ABOUT HOW THEY'RE GOING
TO PAY THIS BILL OR HOW THEY'RE
GOING TO PAY THAT BILL.
I DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT THAT
NOW.
THAT STRESS IS OFF MY FAMILY AND
THAT IS A GREAT RELIEF AND I
HAVE SPENT MY ENTIRE LIFE AND
HOPEFULLY WILL CONCLUDE MY
POLITICAL LIFE IN THE WHITE
HOUSE TRYING TO MAKE SURE THAT
EVERY PERSON IN THIS COUNTRY
DOES NOT HAVE TO DEAL WITH THE
STRESS OF WHETHER THEY CAN
AFFORD TO PAY THE ELECTRIC BILL,
WHETHER THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE
HEALTH CARE, WHETHER THEY CAN
SEND THEIR KIDS TO CHILD CARE.
SO THAT IS THE DIFFERENCE THAT I
HAVE LEARNED.
IT'S GREAT NOT TO HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT WHETHER YOUR ELECTRICITY
OR PHONE BILL IS GOING TO BE
SHUT OFF AND I WANT EVERY PERSON
IN THIS COUNTRY, THE WEALTHIEST
COUNTRY IN THE HISTORY OF THE
WORLD TO BE ABLE TO LIVE IN THAT
KIND OF WAY.
>> NEXT QUESTION, SOPHOMORE AT
HARVARD STUDYING GOVERNMENT FROM
MINNESOTA.
GABRIEL.
>> HI, SENATOR.
WHAT IS ONE THING THAT YOU HAVE
CHANGED YOUR MIND ABOUT
RECENTLY?
>> NOTHING.
I'VE BEEN CON SISTENT FOR -- JUT
KIDDING.
I HAVE BEEN PAYING MORE
ATTENTION TO FOREIGN POLICY.
I WAS RIGHTFULLY CRITICIZED THE
LAST TIME AROUND BECAUSE I
DIDN'T PAY AS MUCH ATTENTION AS
I MIGHT.
THE ECONOMY ISSUES, WHETHER
PEOPLE HAVE HEALTH CARE AND
WHETHER THEY HAVE DECENT PAYING
JOBS AND DEAL WITH CLIMATE
CHANGE IS ENORMOUSLY IMPORTANT
BUT WE HAVE TO LOOK AT THE
UNITED STATES'S ROLE IN THE
WORLD AS WELL AND PROBABLY A FEW
YEARS AGO I WOULD NOT HAVE BEEN
AS INVOLVED AS I HAVE RECENTLY
BEEN IN DEMANDING AND HELPING IN
THE SENATE TO PASS A RESOLUTION
TO GET THE UNITED STATES OUT OF
THE SAUDI LEAD INTERVENTION IN
YEMEN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND FOR THE FIRST TIME IN 45
YEARS UNDER THE WAR POWERS ACT,
IT HAS BEEN SUCCESSFULLY USED.
WE DID IT IN THE SENATE AND WE
DID IT IN THE HOUSE.
SADLY, TRAGICALLY TRUMP VETOED
IT.
BUT TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTION MORE
ABOUT FOREIGN POLICY ISSUES THAN
I PREVIOUSLY DID.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GOOD PLACE TO STOP.
WE'LL TAKE A QUICK BREAK.
PLEASE COME BACK.
WE HAVE A LOT MORE OF CNN'S
SPECIAL DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
TOWN HALL EVENT RIGHT NOW WITH
SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS.
GO NOWHERE.
Who's idea was this?
♪
At Fidelity, we make sure you
have a clear plan
to cover the essentials
in retirement,
as well as all the things
you want to do.
Because when you're ready
for what comes next,
the only direction is forward.
Red Lobster's new
Weekday Win Menu is here:
Five Days.
Five Deals.
For Fifteen Dollars
Get a different deal
every weekday
til six pm
Like Endless Shrimp Monday
Admiral's Feast Tuesday
Four course feast Wednesday
and more.
Five Days.
Five Deals.
Fifteen dollars.
See you before six.
Now, New York inspired shades.
Super Stay Matte Ink
from Maybelline New York.
Bold color.
Urban edge.
Liquid matte
formula.
Up to 16
hour wear.
Super Stay Matte Ink.
Only from Maybelline New York.
♪
With Venus, you're in charge of
your skin.
So, write your own rules.
Because no one gets an opinion
on why you shave -
or how you show your skin.
♪
If you see traces of blood
when you brush or floss,
you don't have to choose
between healthy gums
and strong teeth.
Complete Protection
from parodontax
has 8 designed benefits for
healthy gums and strong teeth.
Complete Protection
from parodontax.
This is the story of John Smith.
Not this John Smith.
Or this John Smith.
Or any of the other
hundreds of John Smiths
that are Humana Medicare
Advantage members.
No, it's this John Smith.
Who we paired with a Humana
team member to help address
his own specific health needs.
At Humana, we take a personal
approach to your health,
to provide care that's just
as unique as you are.
No matter what your name is.
♪
Feel the clarity of
non-drowsy Claritin
and relief from
Symptoms caused
No matter what your name is.
by over
200 indoor
and outdoor
allergens.
Like those
from buddy.
Because stuffed
animals
are clearly no substitute
for real ones.
Feel the clarity.
And Live Claritin clear.
Six months, six pushups ready.
Up.
Down.
Ah ah!
That's one.
Up.
That's two.
Down.
Get down,
get down.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO CNN'S
SPECIAL DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
TOWN HALL EVENT.
WE'RE LIVE ON THE CAMPUS IN
MANCHESTER, NEW HAMPSHIRE.
RIGHT NOW WE'RE TALKING WITH
SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS.
QUESTION ABOUT THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION.
IT WAS INTERESTING TO HEAR YOUR
COLLEAGUE SENATOR ELIZABETH
WARREN SAY ON THIS STAGE
EARLIER, YOU KNOW, THERE IS NO
POLITICAL INCONVENIENCE
EXCEPTION TO THE UNITED STATES
CONSTITUTION.
HER ARGUMENT WAS IF ANY OTHER
HUMAN BEING IN THIS COUNTRY HAD
DONE WHAT IS DOCUMENTED IN THE
MUELLER REPORT THEY WOULD BE
ARRESTED AND PUT IN JAIL AND HE
IS OBVIOUSLY REFERENCING THIS
PRESIDENT.
DO YOU AGREE THAT IT IS TIME FOR
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS AS SHE
SAYS?
>> WELL, WHAT I AGREE IS THAT WE
HAVE THE MOST DANGEROUS
PRESIDENT IN THE MODERN HISTORY
OF THIS COUNTRY.
SOMEBODY WHO IS A PATHOLOGICAL
LIAR.
SOMEBODY WHO THE MUELLER REPORT
SAID LEFT THE QUESTION OPEN
WHICH CONGRESS HAS TO EXPLORE AS
TO WHETHER OR NOT HE OBSTRUCTED
JUSTICE.
A VERY SERIOUS CRIME.
TO MY VIEW IS TWOFOLD.
FIRST IT GOES WITHOUT SAYING
THAT THE CONGRESS HAS GOT TO
TAKE A HARD LOOK AT THAT AND DO
A HARD INVESTIGATION AND ASK --
SUBPOENA THE PEOPLE WHO WERE
MENTIONED IN THAT REPORT AND GET
TO THE TRUTH.
DID TRUMP ACTUALLY OBSTRUCT
JUSTICE?
BUT HERE IS MY CONCERN.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, WHAT IS
MOST IMPORTANT TO ME IS TO SEE
TO EVERYTHING■E SURE THAT THAT .
BUT IF FOR THE NEXT YEAR ALL THE
CONGRESS IS TALKING ABOUT IS
TRUMP, TRUMP, TRUMP, AND MUELLER
MUELLER, MUELLER AND WE'RE NOT
TALKING ABOUT HEALTH CARE AND
RAISING THE MINIMUM WAGE TO A
LIVING WAGE AND WE'RE NOT
TALKING ABOUT CLIMATE CHANGE AND
SEXISM AND RACISM AND HOMOPHOBIA
AND THE ISSUES THAT CONCERN
ORDINARY AMERICANS, I WORRY THAT
WORKS TO TRUMP'S ADVANTAGE.
I THINK THERE HAS TO BE A
THOROUGH INVESTIGATION.
THE HOUSE DEMOCRATS WILL DO IT.
I'D APPRECIATE IF MY REPUBLICAN
COLLEAGUES IN THE SENATE HAD THE
GUTS TO DO IT AS WELL BUT I
WON'T HOLD MY BREATH.
I WANT TO SEE THAT
INVESTIGATION.
WE'LL SEE WHERE IT GOES BUT
RIGHT NOW, YOU KNOW, THAT'S IT.
>> SO YOU DON'T KNOW WHERE YOU
ARE ON IMPEACHMENT YET BUT WHAT
IF YOU REVERSE YOUR ARGUMENT AND
SAY YOU JUST HAD THAT ANSWERED
TWICE.
MUELLER SAID HE COULDN'T COME TO
A CONCLUSION.
HE CAN'T EXONERATE AND CAN'T
PROSECUTE AND YOU HAD THE DEPUTY
AG SAY NO OBSTRUCTION.
YOU GOT YOUR ANSWER TWICE.
WHY LOOK AGAIN?
>> NO, THE ISSUE OF OBSTRUCTION,
MUELLER SAID THAT'S AN OPEN
QUESTION AND THAT'S SOMETHING
THE HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES
SHOULD LOOK AT.
>> AND THE AG AND DEPUTY AG SAID
NO OBSTRUCTION.
>> I'D RATHER HAVE AN OBJECTIVE
INVESTIGATION DONE BY THE HOUSE.
>> NEXT QUESTION.
SAMANTHA IS A SOPHOMORE AT
HARVARD STUDYING SOCIAL STUDIES
FROM CALIFORNIA.
>> I HAVE A SNEAKING SUSPICION
THAT I DIDN'T SAY YOUR NAME
RIGHT.
IT'S NOT EVEN CLOSE TO WHAT I
SAID.
>> A LIFETIME OF IT.
IT'S OKAY.
HI SENATOR SANDERS, SO MY
FATHER'S FAMILY LEFT SOVIET
RUSSIA IN 1979 FLEAEING FROM TH
SAME SOCIALIST POLICIES YOU SEEM
EAGER TO PUT IN THIS COUNTRY.
HOW DO YOU RECTIFY IT WITH THE
FAILURES OF SOCIALISM IN EVERY
COUNTRY THAT HAS TRIED IT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THANK YOU FOR THAT QUESTION.
IS IT YOUR ASSUMPTION THAT I
BELIEVED IN AUTHORITARIAN
COMMUNISM THAT WAS IN THE SOVIET
UNION.
I HAVEN'T AND I OPPOSED IT.
I BELIEVE IN A VIGOROUS POLICY.
YOU ASKED ME ABOUT DEMOCRATIC
SOCIALISM.
FAIR QUESTION AND LET ME ANSWER
IT.
I HAPPEN TO BELIEVE THAT IN THE
UNITED STATES THERE IS SOMETHING
FUNDAMENTALLY WRONG WHEN WE HAVE
THREE FAMILIES OWNING MORE
WEALTH THAN THE BOTTOM HALF OF
AMERICAN SOCIETY.
160 MILLION PEOPLE.
SOMETHING WRONG WHEN THE TOP 1%
OWNS MORE WEALTH THAN THE BOTTOM
92%.
SOMETHING VERY WRONG WHEN 49% OF
ALL NEW INCOME TODAY IS GOING TO
THE TOP 1%.
AND SOMETHING IS EQUALLY WRONG
WHEN WE HAVE A CORRUPT POLITICAL
SYSTEM MADE WORSE BY THIS
DISASTROUS CITIZEN'S UNITED
SUPREME COURT DECISION THAT
ALLOWS BILLIONAIRES TO SPEND
UNLIMITED SUMS OF MONEY TO ELECT
CANDIDATES THAT REPRESENT THE
WEALTHY.
SO ANSWER NUMBER ONE, IT'S A
RADICAL IDEA.
MAYBE NOT EVERYBODY AGREES BUT I
HAPPEN TO BELIEVE WE SHOULD HAVE
A GOVERNMENT THAT REPRESENTS
WORKING FAMILIES AND NOT JUST
THE 1% AND POWERFUL
CORPORATIONS.
THAT'S POINT NUMBER ONE.
POINT NUMBER TWO, WHAT DO I MEAN
WHEN I TALK ABOUT DEMOCRATIC
SOCIALISM?
IT'S CERTAINLY NOT THE
AUTHORITARIAN COMMUNISM THAT
EXISTED IN THE SOVIET UNION.
THIS IS WHAT IT MEANS.
IT MEANS THAT WE CHERISH AMONG
OTHER THINGS OUR BILL OF RIGHTS.
FRANKLIN ROOSEVELT MADE THIS
POINT.
IN 1944 IN A STATE OF THE UNION
ADDRESS THAT NEVER GOT A LOT OF
ATTENTION, THIS IS WHAT HE SAID
BASICALLY.
A VERY PROFOUND SPEECH.
HE SAID WE GOT A GREAT
CONSTITUTION.
BILL OF RIGHTS PROTECTS YOUR
FREEDOM OF RELIGION.
FREEDOM OF ASSEMBLY, FREEDOM OF
SPEECH BUT IT DOESN'T PROTECT
AND GUARANTEE YOU ECONOMIC
RIGHTS.
SO LET ME BE HONEST WITH YOU, I
BELIEVE IN A DEMOCRATIC
CIVILIZED SOCIETY HEALTH CARE IS
A HUMAN RIGHT.
GOVERNMENT SHOULD MAKE THAT
HAPPEN.
I BELIEVE THAT EVERY YOUNG
PERSON IN THIS COUNTRY
REGARDLESS OF HIS OR HER INCOME
HAS THE RIGHT TO GET ALL THE
EDUCATION THEY NEED.
THAT'S WHY I HAVE FOUGHT HARD
WITH SOME SUCCESS TO MOVE TOWARD
MAKING PUBLIC COLLEGES AND
UNIVERSITIES TUITION FREE AND
VERY SUBSTANTIALLY REDUCE
STUDENT DEBT.
AND I BELIEVE THERE'S SOMETHING
WRONG WHEN YOU HAVE MILLIONS OF
FAMILIES PAYING 40 OR 50% OF
THEIR LIMITED INCOMES TO PUT A
ROOF OVER THEIR HEADS AND THAT
MILLIONS OF WORKING CLASS
FAMILIES, YOUNG PARENTS CANNOT
FIND QUALITY AND AFFORDABLE
CHILD CARE.
SO WE HAVE TO ADDRESS THE VERY,
VERY RICH GETTING RICHER AND
MIDDLE CLASS STRUGGLING AND 40
MILLION LIVING IN POVERTY.
IT MEANS TO ME THAT WE EXPAND
MEDICARE AND PROVIDE EDUCATIONAL
OPPORTUNITY FOR ALL AMERICANS.
WE REBUILD OUR CRUMBLING
INFRASTRUCTURE.
IN OTHER WORDS GOVERNMENT SERVES
THE NEEDS OF ALL PEOPLE RATHER
THAN JUST WEALTHY CAMPAIGN
CONTRIBUTORS.
THAT'S WHAT IT MEANS TO ME.
>> YOU WERE ASKED EARLIER ON AS
A QUICK FOLLOW UP TO THIS, WHAT
DO YOU FEEL DIFFERENTLY ABOUT
NOW?
YOU USED TO ARGUE THAT YOU
SHOULD HAVE GOVERNMENT CONTROL
THE MEANS OF CAPITALISM.
>> WHEN DID I SAY THAT?
>> IN THE 70s.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY IN THE 70s?
>> GAGA GOO GOO.
WHAT I'M SAYING IS YOU HAVE
CHANGED.
>> WAIT A MINUTE, FIRST OF ALL,
HE HEARS ME CRITICIZING MEDIA
ALL THE TIME AND HE GETS NERVOUS
ABOUT IT.
>> ONE OF MANY THINGS THAT MAKES
ME NERVOUS.
>> I WAS A MAYOR OF A CITY FOR 8
YEARS.
I SAID WHAT I SAID AND THAT IS
THAT I WANT TO LIVE IN A NATION
IN WHICH ALL PEOPLE IN THE
WEALTHIEST NATION OF THE HISTORY
OF THE WORLD CAN HAVE A DECENT
STANDARD OF LIVING.
I'M NOT THINKING ABOUT EVERYBODY
OWNING A BIG FANCY HOUSE OR
CADILLAC OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
BUT THE IDEAS ARE NOT TO
RADICAL.
HEALTH CARE AS A RIGHT EXISTS IN
VIRTUALLY ANY OTHER MAJOR
COUNTRY ON EARTH.
DOES ANYONE HERE KNOW HOW MUCH
IT COSTS TO GO TO COLLEGE IN
GERMANY?
IT'S.
I SAID IN FINLAND COLLEGE IS
FREE.
HE SAID IT'S NOT FREE.
HE SAID THEY PAY US TO GO TO
COLLEGE.
SO THESE ARE IDEAS ABOUT
GUARANTEEING ECONOMIC RIGHTS TO
WORKING PEOPLE RATHER THAN
SEEING PEOPLE WORKING TWO OR
THREE JOBS, $8 OR $9 AN HOUR
LIVING UNDER GREAT STRESS AND
MARRIAGES DISSOLVING AS A
RESULT.
THAT'S WHAT I BELIEVE.
I BELIEVE IN A NATION IN WHICH
WE GUARANTEE FUNDAMENTAL
ECONOMIC RIGHTS, BASIC
NECESSITIES OF LIFE.
>> YOU SAID YOU HAVLSO BEEN
THINKING MORE ABOUT FOREIGN
POLICY.
LET'S GET A QUESTION ON THAT.
SHELLY, A JUNIOR AT HARVARD
>> AS A YOUNG MAN ABOUT YOUR AGE
I SPENT A NUMBER OF MONTHS IN
ISRAEL.
I HAVE FAMILY IN ISRAEL.
I AM NOT ANTIISRAEL BUT THE FACT
OF THE MATTER IS THAT NETANYAHU
IS A RIGHT WING POLITICIAN WHO I
THINK IS TREATING THE
PALESTINIAN PEOPLE EXTREMELY
UNFAIRLY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> SO WHAT I BELIEVE IS THE
UNITED STATES GIVES BILLIONS OF
DOLLARS IN MILITARY AID TO
ISRAEL.
WHAT I BELIEVE IS NOT RADICAL.
I JUST BELIEVE THAT THE UNITED
STATES SHOULD DEAL WITH THE
MIDDLE EAST ON A LEVEL PLAYING
FIELD BASIS.
IN OTHER WORDS, THE GOAL MUST BE
TO TRY TO BRING PEOPLE TOGETHER
AND NOT JUST SUPPORT ONE
COUNTRY, WHICH IS NOW RUN BY A
RIGHT WING, DARE I SAY, RACIST
GOVERNMENT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> SO I AM 100% PRO-ISRAEL.
THEY HAVE EVERY RIGHT IN THE
WORLD TO EXIST AND TO EXIST IN
PEACE AND SECURITY AND NOT BE
SUBJECTED THE TERRORIST ATTACKS
BUT THE UNITED STATES NEEDS TO
DEAL NOT JUST WITH ISRAEL BUT
WITH THE PALESTINIAN PEOPLE AS
WELL.
>> ANOTHER QUESTION, NICHOLAS
ST. GERMAIN.
HE'S AN ASPIRING POLICE OFFICER.
>> GOOD.
>> WHAT IS YOUR STANCE ON
PUTTING ARMED GUARDS OR
HEIGHTENED POLICE PRESENCE
INSIDE OF SCHOOLS?
>> I'M AGAINST IT.
BUT LET ME ALSO --
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> LET ME SAY THIS TO NICHOLAS
AND TO A LOT OF YOUNG PEOPLE, WE
NEED FUNDAMENTAL REFORM IN OUR
CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM WHICH IS
VERY, VERY BROKEN NOW.
AND I'M DELIGHTED TO HEAR THAT
YOU'RE GOING INTO CRIMINAL
JUSTICE.
WE NEED A LOT OF YOUNG PEOPLE TO
GET INVOLVED IN CRIMINAL JUSTICE
AND TO HELP US TRANSFORM A
CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM THAT IS
NOT WORKING RIGHT NOW.
WE HAVE MORE PEOPLE IN JAIL THAN
ANY OTHER MAJOR COUNTRY ON
EARTH.
MORE PEOPLE IN JAIL THAN CHINA
DOES.
DISPROPORTIONALLY AFRICAN
AMERICAN, LATINO, AND NATIVE
AMERICANS.
WE HAVE GOT TO INVEST, IN MY
VIEW, IN MY VIEW WE HAVE GOT TO
INVEST IN OUR YOUNG PEOPLE IN
JOBS AND EDUCATION.
WE HAVE A LOT OF KIDS HANGING
OUT ON STREET CORNERS.
THEY'RE GOING TO GET INVOLVED IN
DESTRUCTIVE AND SELF-DESTRUCTIVE
ACTIVITY.
IT MAKES MORE SENSE TO ME AT A
TIME WHEN WE'RE SPENDING $80
BILLION A YEAR LOCKING FELLOW
AMERICANS UP, WE HAVE TO END THE
SO-CALLED WAR ON DRUGS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> MANY LIVES HAVE BEEN
DESTROYED BECAUSE OF CRIMINAL
RECORDS ASSOCIATED WITH
POSSESSION OF MARIJUANA AND I'M
DELIGHTED TO SEE THAT NOT ONLY
STATE AFTER STATE ARE LEGALIZING
MARIJUANA BUT ALSO SOME
COMM MOVING TO EXPONGE
THE RECORDS OF PEOPLE IN
POSSESSION OF MARIJUANA.
BUT ALSO WE NEED POLICE
DEPARTMENT REFORM AND WHAT THAT
MEANS IS WE HAVE A LOT OF
DEPARTMENTS THAT SPEND MORE TIME
ON TEACHING THE OFFICERS HOW TO
SHOOT A GUN AND LESS TIME ON
TEACHING THEM HOW TO BREAK UP
DISTURBANCES IN A NON-LETHAL
WAY.
BEING A COP IS AN ENORMOUSLY
IMPORTANT JOB AND DIFFICULT JOB
AND MOST POLICE OFFICERS TO MY
MIND, I WAS A MAYOR FOR YEARS.
THEY'RE TRYING HARD AND TRYING
TO DO THE RIGHT THING UNDER VERY
DIFFICULT CIRCUMSTANCES.
BUT ONE OF THE POINTS THAT WE
SHOULD MAKE AND AS PRESIDENT I
WILL HELP LEAD THAT EFFORT IS
THAT LETHAL FORCE, USE OF A
WEAPON TO KILL SOMEBODY SHOULD
BE THE LAST RESPONSE, NOT AS IS
TOO OFTEN THE CASE, THE FIRST
RESPONSE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S BRING IN GEORGIA.
GE
GEORGIA IS A SOPHOMORE HERE
STUDYING ENVIRONMENTAL SCIENCE
FROM PENNSYLVANIA.
THANK YOU.
>> HI, SENATOR.
GIVEN THE CURRENT POLITICAL
CLIMATE IN A NATION THAT'S SO
POLARIZED WHAT WILL YOU DO TO
REACH ACROSS THE AISLE TO
COMPROMISE WITH THE GOP?
>> WELL, I HAVE DONE THAT
THROUGHOUT MY POLITICAL CAREER.
IT MAY SURPRISE SOME PEOPLE BUT
THERE WERE YEARS WHEN I WAS IN
THE U.S. HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES THAT I PASSED
MORE AMENDMENTS IN A GIVEN YEAR
THAN ANY OTHER CONGRESSMAN
BECAUSE I REACHED ACROSS THE
AISLE AND FOUND COMMON GROUND
WITH REPUBLICANS WHO AGREED WITH
ME ON A PARTICULAR ISSUE AND I
MENTIONED A MOMENT AGO THAT I
WAS VERY PROUD TO HAVE HELPED
PASS RESOLUTION IN THE SENATE TO
GET THE UNITED STATES OUT OF THE
WAR IN YEMEN AND THE CO-SPONSOR
WAS A VERY CONSERVATIVE
REPUBLICAN FROM UTAH NAMED MIKE
LEE AND I THINK THAT IF THERE IS
GOOD LEADERSHIP IN THE WHITE
HOUSE, IT TURNS OUT THAT THERE
IS A LOT MORE COCOMMONALITY OF
INTERESTS THAN THE MEDIA OFTEN
PORTRAYS AND WE CAN BRING PEOPLE
TOGETHER ON THAT.
FOR EXAMPLE, WHETHER YOU'RE A
REPUBLICAN OR DEMOCRAT OR AN
INDEPENDENT, YOU KNOW THERE'S
SOMETHING WRONG WHEN OUR
INFRASTRUCTURE IS CRUMBLING.
OUR ROADS AND BRIDGES AND WASTE
WATER PLANTS.
I BELIEVE I CAN BRING
REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS
TOGETHER TO SAY YOU KNOW WHAT,
IF WE REBUILD OUR CRUMBLING
INFRASTRUCTURE WE MAKE SURE THAT
EVERY AMERICAN FAMILY HAS CLEAN
DRINKING WATER AND PEOPLE'S CARS
DON'T GET DESTROYED WHEN THEY GO
THROUGH A POTHOLE, I THINK WE
CAN HAVE REPUBLICAN SUPPORT FOR
A SENSIBLE INFRASTRUCTURE
PROGRAM.
ANOTHER EXAMPLE, THIS COUNTRY
AND I THINK EVERYBODY
UNDERSTANDS IT IS BEING RIPPED
OFF BY THE PHARMACEUTICAL
INDUSTRY.
WE PAY THE HIGHEST PRICES IN THE
WORLD FOR PRESCRIPTION DRUGS.
THE TEN MAJOR PHARMACEUTICAL
COMPANIES MADE $69 BILLION IN
PROFIT AND YET ONE IN FIVE
AMERICANS CAN'T AFFORD THE
MEDICINE THEY NEED.
THEY ARE INCREDIBLY GREEDY I
THINK A NUMBER OF REPUBLICANS
KNOW THAT AND I THINK THAT WE
CAN WORK TOGETHER AND WE HAVE
VERY SPECIFIC IDEAS TO DO THAT
TO CUT PRESCRIPTION DRUG COSTS
IN THIS COUNTRY IN HALF SO THAT
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ARE NOT
PAYING ANY MORE.
>> LET'S HOLD IT THERE AND TAKE
A BREAK.
WHEN WE COME BACK WE HAVE MORE
WITH SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS.
STAY WITH CNN.
♪
There goes our first big order.
44, 45, 46...
How many of these
did they order?
Ooh, that's hot.
♪
You know, we could sell these.
Nah.
♪
We don't bake.
Opportunity.
What we deliver by delivering.
New Lysol Wipes are crazy
strong.
Don't believe us?
We got this workout class to
compare them to Clorox.
Wow!
Feel the strength
of new Lysol Wipes.
Dude!
Are you looking at this?
Can I take those?
No.
Lysol. What it takes
to protect.®
(ding)
Hey, who are you?
Oh, hey Jeff, I'm a car thief...
What?!
I'm here to
steal your car because,
well, that's my job.
What?
What??
WHAT?!
(laughing)
What??
WHAT?!
What?!
[crash]
WHAT?!
Haha, it happens.
And if you've got
cut-rate car insurance,
paying for this could
feel like getting robbed twice.
So get Allstate...
and be better protected
from Mayhem...
like me.
♪
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it
from your allergy pills?
Flonase relieves
your worst symptoms
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
Flonase helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances.
Most pills only block one.
Flonase.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
WE'RE LIVE IN NEW HAMPSHIRE FOR
CNN'S SPECIAL DEMOCRATIC TOWN
HALL.
WE'RE LIVE WITH BERNIE SANDERS
FROM VERMONT.
HOW ABOUT TAXES.
LET'S BRING IN KYLE FROM RHODE
ISLAND.
HE'S A FRESHMAN HERE STUDYING
CL
CLASSICAL ARCHAEOLOGY.
>> YOUR PLAN FOR FREE COLLEGE
APPEALS TO MANY STUDENTS HERE.
ONE OF THE METHODS YOU PROPOSED
WOULD BE THROUGH RAISING TAXES
ON THE WEALTHY.
BECAUSE PEOPLE WITH A COLLEGE
EDUCATION TEND TO HAVE HIGHER
INCOMES COULD THIS PLAN
EVENTUALLY HURT US?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
I THINK WHAT OUR CAMPAIGN IS
ABOUT IS JUSTICE.
IT'S A FIGHT FOR JUSTICE.
ECONOMIC JUSTICE, SOCIAL
JUSTICE, RACIAL JUSTICE,
ENVIRONMENTAL JUSTICE AND AT THE
END OF THE DAY YOU HAVE TO ASK
YOURSELF WHETHER IT'S ACCEPTABLE
THAT CORPORATIONS LIKE AMAZON,
NETFLIX, GENERAL MOTORS PAY
NOTHING IN FEDERAL TAXES.
WHETHER TRUMP'S TAX PROPOSAL
GIVES MASSIVE TAX BREAKS TO
FAMILIES LIKE THE KOCH BROTHERS.
ONE OF THE WEALTHIEST FAMILIES
IN AMERICA.
SO I THINK WHAT WE NEED IS A
FAIR AND PROGRESSIVE TAX SYSTEM
IN ORDER TO RAISE THE REVENUE
THAT WE NEED TO HELP WORKING
FAMILIES.
SO I HAVE NO APOLOGIES TO MAKE
TO SAY WE'RE GOING TO DO OUR
BEST TO END THE TAX HAVENS THAT
EXIST IN BERMUDA AND OTHER
COUNTRIES.
AND THEN THEY'RE CUTTING BACK ON
EDUCATION AND HEALTH CARE.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE A LOT OF SENSE
TO ME.
SO I DO BELIEVE THAT VERY
WEALTHY PEOPLE AND PROFITABLE
CORPORATIONS SHOULD BEGIN TO PAY
THEIR FAIR SHARE OF TAXES.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU, TRUMP'S TAX
PROPOSAL THAT GAVE A TRILLION TO
THE TOP 1% AND LARGE PROFITABLE
CORPORATIONS DRIVING UP THE
DEFICIT WAS AN OUTRAGE.
IF ELECTED PRESIDENT I WILL
RESCIND THOSE TAX BREAKS.
>> SENATOR WARREN OBVIOUSLY ON
EARLY TONIGHT ARGUABLY GOES
FURTHER THAN YOU BECAUSE SHE HAS
A PIECE IN HER PLAN ABOUT DEBT
FORGI
FORGIVENESS.
IF YOUR FAMILY MAKES 100,000 OR
LESS YOU CAN FORGIVE UP TO
50,000 IN STUDENT LOANS.
DO YOU SUPPORT HER PLAN?
>> I HAVEN'T STUDIED IT BUT I
THINK ELIZABETH AND I END UP
AGREEING ON A WHOLE LOT OF
ISSUES AND WHAT SHE UNDERSTANDS
AND WHAT I UNDERSTAND IS WE
DON'T PUNISH PEOPLE FOR THE
CRIME OF GETTING A HIGHER
EDUCATION.
>> I HAVE YOUNG PEOPLE FROM
HOWARD UNIVERSITY THAT ARE
TEACHERS IN MY OFFICE A COUPLE
OF WEEKS AGO.
THIS FELLOW WORKING AS A TEACHER
GETTING HIS MASTERS DEGREE.
$182,000 IN DEBT.
HOW DO YOU PAY THAT OFF ON A
TEACHER'S SALARY.
I TALKED TO A YOUNG DOCTOR,
$300,000 IN DEBT.
SO WE HAVE TO DO AS I SAID
EARLIER, TWO THINGS.
I'M PROUD.
I RAISED THIS ISSUE.
FOUR YEARS AGO.
EVERYBODY FOUR YEARS AGO SAYS
BERNIE IS A LITTLE BIT CRAZY,
TALKING ABOUT MAKING PUBLIC
COLLEGES AND UNIVERSITIES
TUITION FREE.
AIN'T SUCH A CRAZY IDEA TODAY.
WE CAN ARGUE ABOUT THE BEST WAY
TO DO IT.
AND WE HAVE MANY DIFFERENCES ON
IT.
PEOPLE SHOULD NOT HAVE TO FORGO
GETTING MARRIED OR A CAR FOR
HAVING A COLLEGE EDUCATION.
PEOPLE SAY HOW ARE YOU GOING TO
PAY FOR THAT?
GET BACK TO THE QUESTION THAT
THE YOUNG MAN ASKED A MOMENT
AGO.
YEAH, WHEN WALL STREET WAS
BAILED OUT BY CONGRESS TO THE
TUNE OF AT LEAST $1 TRILLION,
DON'T TELL ME WE DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH MONEY IN THIS COUNTRY TO
SUBSTANTIALLY' REDUCE STUDENT
DEBT.
>> ANOTHER QUESTION.
SHE'S A FRESHMAN AT HARVARD
STUDYING GOVERNMENT AND
ECONOMICS.
SHE'S FROM CALIFORNIA.
WHAT IS YOUR QUESTION.
>> HI, SENATOR SANDERS.
THE GREEN NEW DEAL REALLY
ENERGIZED THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
RECENTLY AND WHILE I COMPLETELY
AGREE THAT CLIMATE CHANGE NEEDS
TO BE ONE OF OUR TOP PRIORITIES,
MY CONCERN HAS BEEN LACK OF
SPECIFICITY AND DETAILED
POLICIES AS TO HOW WE WILL
ACTUALLY BECOME CARBON NEUTRAL.
WHAT ARE SPECIFIC REFORMS YOU
HAVE AND HOW WILL YOU ENSURE
THAT FEASIBLE SUPPORT IS GIVEN
TO CARBON HEAVY INDUSTRIES THAT
WILL BE MOST IMPACTED TO EASE
THAT TRANSITION.
>> GOOD.
EXCELLENT QUESTION.
ALL THE OTHERS WERE EXCELLENT
TOO.
THIS IS WHERE I COME FROM ON
THIS ISSUE AND I HAVE TO TELL
YOU A NUMBER OF YEARS AGO I
INTRODUCED THE MOST SWEEPING
LEGISLATION TO COMBAT CLIMATE
CHANGE IN THE HISTORY OF THE
SENATE.
HERE'S WHERE WE ARE.
YOU KNOW THIS, THE SCIENTISTS
KNOW THE ISSUE THE BEST.
SOME MONTHS AGO MADE IT CLEAR
THAT IF WE DO NOT SIGNIFICANTLY
TRANSFORM OUR ENERGY SYSTEM AWAY
FROM FOSSIL FUELS AND ENERGY
EFFICIENCY AND SUSTAINABLE
ENERGIES, THIS PLANET AND OUR
COUNTRY SUFFER IRREPARABLE
DAMAGE.
SO TO ME, THE ISSUE OF MOVING
VERY AGGRESSIVELY ON CLIMATE
CHANG IS A MORAL ISSUE BECAUSE
IT SPEAKS TO WHETHER OR NOT WE
ARE GOING TO LEAVE THIS COUNTRY
AND OUR PLANET AND I'VE GOT
SEVEN GRANDCHILDREN INCLUDING
THREE HERE IN NEW HAMPSHIRE IN A
WAY THAT IS HEALTHY AND
HABITABLE.
AND IF WE DO NOT ACT
AGGRESSIVELY IT WILL BE A
DISASTER IN MY VIEW FOR THE
ENTIRE PLANET AND THE UNITED
STATES.
TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTION, WHAT
DOES THAT MEAN?
IT MEANS THAT WE HAVE GOT TO
TAKE ON THE FOSSIL FUEL INDUSTRY
AND MAKE IT VERY CLEAR THAT WE
ARE MOVING AWAY FROM FOSSIL FUEL
AND AT THE SAME TIME NOT BLAMING
THOSE PEOPLE WHO WORK IN THE
COAL INDUSTRY OR THE GAS
INDUSTRY OR THE OIL INDUSTRY.
ALL THEY'RE TRYING TO DO IS FEED
THEIR FAMILIES.
AND WE SUPPORT THAT.
SO WE IN ALL OF THE LEGISLATION,
WE HAVE MANY, MANY MILLIONS OF
DOLLARS TO GO INTO THOSE
COMMUNITIES TO HELP WORKERS GET
THE TRAINING AND THE EDUCATION
THAT THEY NEED TO GET JOBS THAT
WILL PAY THEM AS MUCH AND EVEN
MORE.OVE AGGRESSIVELY TOWARD
ENERGY EFFICIENCY.
ONE OF THE POINTS THE GREEN NEW
DEAL MAKES IS WE HAVE THE
POTENTIAL TO CREATE MILLIONS OF
GOOD PAYING JOBS AS WE TRANSFORM
OUR ENERGY SYSTEM AWAY FROM
FOSSIL FUEL.
THERE ARE BUILDINGS ALL OVER NEW
ENGLAND, HOMES ALL OVER NEW
ENGLAND THAT ARE WASTING AN
ENORMOUS AMOUNT OF ENERGY.
WE CAN WEATHERIZE THOSE HOMES.
I'VE BEEN IN HOMES IN VERMONT
WHERE FUEL WENT DOWN BY 50%
BECAUSE PEOPLE GOT THE
INSULATION AND WINDOWS AND
ROOFING THEY NEEDED.
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE CAN BE HELPED
IN THAT RESPECT.
WE SHOULD INVEST VERY
SIGNIFICANTLY IN SOLAR AND IN
WIND.
I KNOW THE PRESIDENT THINKS THAT
WIND TURBINES CAUSE CANCER, ONLY
PERSON IN THE WORLD WHO HAPPENS
TO BELIEVE THAT, BUT WE CAN MOVE
AGGRESSIVELY TOWARD, AND SHOULD.
WIND AND SOLAR, WE HAVE GOT TO
RETHINK OUR TRANSPORTATION
SYSTEM AND BUILD THE KIND OF
STATE OF THE ART RAIL SYSTEM
THAT OUR COUNTRY NEEDS WHICH
WILL HELP US TRANSPORT PEOPLE
AND CARGO IN A MUCH MORE
NONPOLLUTING WAY.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS, THIS IS AN
ISSUE THAT WE CANNOT RUN AWAY
FROM.
AND OF ALL MY DISAGREEMENTS WITH
TRUMP ON VIRTUALLY EVERY ISSUE
THE IDEA THAT HE CONTINUES TO
TALK ABOUT CLIMATE CHANGE AS A
HOAX OR NOT REAL IS SO DANGEROUS
AND SO HARMFUL, NOT ONLY TO OUR
COUNTRY AND THE WORLD, THE
UNITED STATES OF AMERICA UNDER A
SANDERS PRESIDENCY WILL LEAD THE
WORLD IN TRANSFORMING OUR ENERGY
SYSTEM, CREATE MILLIONS OF JOBS,
CREATE A LESS POLLUTING SOCIETY.
AND THAT IS SOMETHING WE HAVE NO
CHOICE BUT IT'S EXACTLY WHAT WE
HAVE TO DO.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S BRING IN
NATHAN WILLIAMS, A SENIOR,
STUDYING EURO SCIENCE AT
HARVARD, FROM CALIFORNIA,
NATHAN.
>> GOOD EVENING, SENATOR
SANDERS.
IF ELECTED YOU WOULD BE THE
OLDEST PRESIDENT IN THE HISTORY
OF THE UNITED STATES YET IN 2016
THE MENIALS FAVORED YOU STRONGLY
OVER HILLARY CLINTON.
WHY DO YOU THINK YOUNG PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN ATTRACTED TO YOUR
CAMPAIGNS AND HOW WILL YOU
ENSURE OUR VOICES ARE
REPRESENTED IN YOUR
ADMINISTRATION.
>> YOUNG PEOPLE ARE VERY SMART,
THAT'S CLEAR.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
THIS IS THE TRUTH, NATHAN, WHEN
WE BEGAN THE 2016 CAMPAIGN IF
ANYBODY THOUGHT WE HAD SOME
DIABOLICAL PLAN, HOW ARE WE
GOING TO REACH OUT TO YOUNG
PEOPLE?
NOT TRUE AT ALL.
IT JUST HAPPENED BECAUSE IT
HAPPENED.
HERE'S WHY I THINK IT HAPPENED.
FIRST OF ALL, YOUR GENERATION IS
THE MOST PROGRESSIVE GENERATION
IN THE HISTORY OF THIS COUNTRY.
YOUR GENERATION MORE THAN ANY
PREVIOUS GENERATION IS
ANTI-RACIST, ANTI-SEXIST, ANTI
HOMOPHOBIA, ANTI RELIGIOUS
BIGOTRY AND YOU SHOULD BE VERY,
VERY PROUD OF THAT.
BUT THE OTHER THING, AND I THINK
THAT MY CAMPAIGN KIND OF SPEAKS
TO THE IDEALISM OF YOUNG PEOPLE
WHO KNOW THAT -- WHO UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S GOING ON TODAY IS NOT --
WE'RE NOT WHERE WE SHOULD BE.
AND YOUNG PEOPLE HAVE A TENDENCY
TO WANT TO THINK BIGGER THAN
OLDER GENERATIONS.
THE SECOND POINT, TO BE MORE
SPECIFIC, YOUR GENERATION,
UNLESS WE TURN THINGS AROUND,
WILL BE THE FIRST GENERATION IN
THE MODERN HISTORY OF AMERICA TO
HAVE A LOWER STANDARD OF LIVING
THAN YOUR PARENTS.
ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT WE HAVE SEEN
IN RECENT YEARS IS AN EXPLOSION
IN TECHNOLOGY.
WE HAVE SEEN AN EXPLOSION IN
WORKER PRODUCTIVITY.
BUT EVERYTHING BEING EQUAL MANY
PEOPLE IN YOUR GENERATION WILL
EARN LESS MONEY THAN YOUR
PARENTS, YOU'RE GOING TO LEAVE
SCHOOL MORE DEEPLY IN DEBT THAN
YOUR PARENTS, YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE A HARDER TIME FINDING
AFFORDABLE HOUSING THAN YOUR
PARENTS.
SO THE ISSUES THAT -- AND YOUR
GENERATION ALSO, OBVIOUSLY, IS
VERY, VERY CONCERNED ABOUT
CLIMATE CHANGE AND RACIAL
JUSTICE AND IMMIGRATION REFORM
AND SO FORTH.
SO I THINK THOSE ARE SOME OF THE
REASONS WHY OUR MESSAGE HAS
RESONATED WITH YOUNG PEOPLE.
>> SENATOR SANDERS, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE THREE TOWN
HALLS DOWN, TWO MORE TO GO
TONIGHT.
A FIVE-HOUR, FIVE CANDIDATE
EVENT.
AT 11:00 P.M. WE'LL BE HEARING
FROM MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIEG ON
THIS STAGE.
WHEN WE COME BACK, SENATOR
KAMALA HARRIS.
DON LEMON 'S GOT THAT ONE, NEXT.
Did you eat all of your treats?
♪ Help! I need somebody
♪ Help! Not just anybody
♪ Help! You know I need someone
BEHR presents: Outdone Yourself.
Staining be done...
and stay done through
every season.
BEHR SEMI-TRANSPARENT STAIN,
overall #1 rated.
Stay done for years to come.
Find it exclusively
at The Home Depot.
With Advil Liqui-Gels,
you'll ask...
What stiff joints?
What bad back?
Advil is... Relief that's
fast. Strength that lasts.
You'll ask...
What pain?
With Advil Liqui-Gels.
-Here comes the rain.
[ Horn honking ]
[ Engine revving ]
What's that, girl?
Flo needs help?!
[ Engine revving ]
Take me to her!
♪♪
Coming, Flo!
Why aren't we taking roads?!
Flo.
[ Horn honking ]
-Oh. You made it.
Do you have change for a dollar?
-This was the emergency?
[ Engine revving ]
Yes, I was busy!
-24-hour roadside assistance.
From America's number-one
motorcycle insurer.
-You know, I think
you're my best friend.
You don't have to say
I'm your best friend.
That's okay.
At Fidelity, we make sure you
have a clear plan
You don't have to say
I'm your best friend.
to cover the essentials
in retirement,
as well as all the things
you want to do.
Because when you're ready
for what comes next,
the only direction is forward.
♪
With Venus, you're in charge of
your skin.
So, write your own rules.
Because no one gets an opinion
on why you shave -
or how you show your skin.
♪
(sobbing)
(speaking in foreign language)
I'm sorry I don't understand...
♪ Help! I need somebody
♪ Help! Not just anybody
♪ Help! You know I need someone
>>> AND WELCOME BACK, EVERYONE,
TO MANCHESTER, NEW HAMPSHIRE,
AND TO THE SPECIAL DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL TOWN HALL.
I'M DON LEMON.
IT'S AN AMAZING NIGHT, FIVE
STRAIGHT TOWN HALLS AND WE'RE
LIVE AND WE THANK THE COLLEGE
FOR HOSTING THIS EVENT.
IT'S BEEN AN AMAZING NIGHT.
FIVE OF THE TOP PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES HAVE SHARING THE SAME
STAGE TONIGHT WITH YOUNG ADULTS
FOR STUDENTS WHO PLAN TO VOTE IN
THEIR STATE AND PRIMARY
CAUCUSES.
WE'VE ALREADY HEARD FROM
SENATORS AMY