>>> HEY, GOOD EVENING.
WELCOME BACK TO NEW HAMPSHIRE.
I'MANDERSON COOPER.
CNN PARTNERED WITH THE HARVARD
UNIVERSITY WITH THE NEW
HAMPSHIRE INSTITUTE OF POLITICS
IN MANCHESTER.■>■>■>
ERHE CANDIDATES ARE TAKING QUES
YOUNG ADULTS WHO PLAN TO VOTE IN
THEY'RE STATE'S DEMOCRATIC
PRIMARY.
YOU'VE HEARD FROM FOUR OF THE
TOP PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES.
BUN BERNIE SANDERS, KAMALA
HARRIS.
NOW IT IS MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIE
GERKS'S TURN.
HE'S SKY ROCKETED TO THE TOP
TIER OF THE DEMOCRATIC FIELD.
HE WAS THE STUDENT PRESIDENT OF
THE HARVARD SCHOOL OF POLITICS
WHILE HE WAS AN UNDERGRADUATE.
BUT HE HAD NO ROLE IN ORGANIZING
THIS EVENT.
PLEASE WELCOME MAYOR BUTTI GERKS
IEG.
WELCOME.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
SO GET RIGHT TO IT.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> FIRST QUESTION FROM A
FRESHMAN IN IDAHO.
>> THANK YOU, MAYOR, FOR TAKING
MY QUESTION.
TREVOR NOAH SAID YOU WERE THE
EXACT OPPOSITE OF TRUMP IN MANY
REGARDS.
GOING SO FAR AS TO SAY YOU WERE
THE ANTITRUMP.
HOWEVER, SIMILARER TO TRUMP YOU
LACK EXPERIENCE.
HOW WOULD YOU USE THIS AS AN
ADVANTAGE?
>> IN MANY WAYS EXPERIENCE IS MY
ANSWERER TO THE QUESTION OF AGE.
I GET MY EXPERIENCE IS NOT THE
MOST CONVENTIONAL BUT UNLIKE
THIS PRESIDENT I HAVE EXPERIENCE
IN GOVERNMENT, AS I OFTEN POINT
OUT.
I GOT NOT ONLY MORE EXPERIENCE
IN GOVERNMENT THAN THE PRESIDENT
BUT MORE EXECUTIVE EXPERIENCE
THAN THE VICE PRESIDENT, MORE
MILITARY EXPERIENCE THAN ANYBODY
IN THE OFFICE SINCE GEORGE H.W.
BUSH.
AND FRANKLY THE LACK OF ACTION
THAT'S HAPPENED ON ISSUES FROM
CLIMATE TO COLLEGE AFFORDABILITY
TO MAKING SURE THAT WE DO
SOMETHING ABOUT THE FISCAL
SUSTAINABILITY OF THIS COUNTRY.
LOOK, EVERYONE COMING INTO THE
OFFICE BRINGS THE COMBINATION OF
LIFE AND PROFESSIONAL
EXPERIENCES THAT THEY HAVE PLUS
THEIR VALUES.
BUT I WOULD ARGUE IT DOESN'T GET
VERY MUCH MORER DIFFERENT.
IT'S NOT POSSIBLE TO BE
DIFFERENT FROM THIS PRESIDENT.
AND I THINK WE NEED A LILT MORE
OF THAT LOCAL PERSPECTIVE.
WHEN I WAS HANGING AROUND, I
DIDN'T THINK A LOT ABOUT LOCAL
GOVERNMENT.
IT WAS USUALLY IN THE PHRASE
STATE AND LOCAL GOVERNMENT.
ALMOST LIKE THEY WERE ONE WORD.
AND ALL I REALLY THOUGHT ABOUT
WAS FEDERAL GOVERNMENT.
BUT WHAT I FOUND IS THERE'S SO
MUCH PURPOSES, SO MUCH MEANING.
AND SO MUCH ACTUAL PROBLEM
SOLVING THAT HAPPENS AT THE
LOCAL LEVEL.
YOU WOULD NEVER HAVE A CITY
GOVERNMENT SHUT DOWN BECAUSE OFF
A DISAGREEMENT OVER POLICY.
IF I HAVE A PROBLEM WITH OUR
COUNSEL, IT WOULD NEVER LEAD TO
THE CITY SHUTTING DOWN BECAUSE
WE'DER DELIVER WATERER.
SO WE SIMPLY FIGURED IT OUT AND
NOW I THINK WE NEED THAT SAME
ATTITUDE TO MAKE ITS WAY INTO
FEDERAL POLITICS BEFORE IT
STARTS HAPPENING THE OTHER WAY
AROUND.
>> YOUR CAMPAIGN WEBSITE HAS GOT
A LOT ABOUT WHAT YOU BELIEVE IN,
YOU YOU ARE.
IT DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING
SPECIFIC ABOUT POLICY.
NOTHING.
NO POLICY SECTION ON IT.
AT WHAT POINT DO YOU NEED TO
START PRESENTING SPECIFIC
POLICIES?
>> I THINK I'VE BEEN PRETTY
CLEAR WHERE I STAND ON MAJOR
ISSUES.
I THINK I LED THE FIELD ON
OPENING THE DEBATE FOR
STRUCTURAL REFORM.
I'D SAY I'VE BEEN MORER SPECIFIC
THAN MANY VERSES JUST SAYING WE
CAN MAKE IT HAPPEN.
AND THERE'S A TOOL COMING ONLINE
SHORTLY THAT WILL MAKE IT
POSSIBLE TO JUST ENTER A KEY
WORD AND SEE, VISUALIZE, PULL
ALL THE VIDEO ON WHAT I'VE SAID
ABOUT THAT PARTICULAR ISSUE.
WE'LL CONTINUE TO ROLL OUT
SPECIFIC POLICY PROPOSALS TOO.
BUT I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT WE
DON'T DROWN PEOPLE BEFORE WE'VE
VINDICATED THE VALUES THAT AN
MATE OUR POLICIES.
WE GO RIGHT TO THE POLICY
PROPOSALS AND WE EXPECT PEOPLE
TO BE ABLE TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
RUR VALUES MUST BE FROM THAT.
I EXPECT IT WILL BE VERY EASY TO
TELL WHERE I STAND ON ISSUES OF
OUR TIME.
BUT I'M GOING TO TAKE TIME LAY
THAT OUT, RATHER THAN COMPETING
STRICTLY ON THE THEORETICAL
ELEMENTS OF THE PROPOSALS
THEMSELVES.
>> BUT IT'S HARD TO COMPARE TO,
LET'S SAY ELIZABETH WARREN WHO'S
OUT HERE.
IT'S NOT -- YOU CAN'T COMPARE
POLICY POSITIONS.
>> SOME OF THAT WILL COME OUT
TONIGHT AND I LOOK FORWARD TO
THAT.
I THINK I'VE WEIGHED IN PRETTY
SPECIFICALLY.
WE'RE IN THE SECOND WEEK OF MY
CAMPAIGN BEING OFFICIAL AND
WE'LL CONTINUE BUILDING OUR
WEBSITE ACCORDINGLY TOO.
>> HANNAH IS A SOPHOMORE AT
BOSTON UNIVERSITY STUDYING
JOURNALISM FROM CALIFORNIA.
>> YOU'VE SAID IN PAST
INTERVIEWS YOU BELIEVE LARGE
CORPORATIONS ARE THE BIGGEST
CHALLENGE FACING AMERICA.
WHAT SPECIFICALLY IS YOUR PLAN
IF YOU BELIEVE TYOU'D LIKE TO
BREAK UP THESE CORPORATIONS,
WHAT LEGISLATIVE ACTION WOULD
YOU TYKE DO SO?
>> THERE'S SEVERAL PROBLEMS IN
OUR RELATIONSHIP TO OUR
DEMOCRACY.
THE WAY CONCENTRATIONS OF WEALTH
AND CORPORATE POWER HAVE TURNED
INTO CONCENTRATIONS OF POLITICAL
POWER AND ONE OF THE REASONS
NEED ACT QUICK 3 ESTABLISH THAT
CORPORATIONS DO NOT EQUAL PEOPLE
AND MONEY DOES NOT EQUAL SPEECH.
SOME HAVE SAID IN THE FRAMEWORK
OF THE CONSTITUTION, YOU CAN'T
FRAME THOSE BOUNDARIES AND THAT
LEAD TO A DECISION I THINK HAS
BEEN DISASTROUS FOR OUR
POLITICS.
I DON'T BELIEVE THE CONSTITUTION
SAYS THAT.
BUT IF THAT'S GOING TO BE THE
DIRECTION THAT OUR FEDERAL
JUDICIARY TAKES GOING FORWARD,
THEN I THINK IT'S NECESSARY TO
FORMER A CONSTITUTIONAL
AMENDMENT AND I'M UNDER NO
ILLUSION IT'S POSSIBLE OVERNIGHT
GET THAT REFORM.
BUT I THINK MOST AMERICANS AGREE
WE NEED TO GET MONEY OUT OF
POLITICS.
THERE'S ISSUES WITH THE SHEER
AGLOMERATION OF DIFFERENT
BUSINESS INTERESTS INTO SINGLE
CORPORATIONS.
BUT PART OF HOW WE REGULATE THAT
IS ACCORDING TO WHETHER THEY'RE
BEHAVING IN AN ANTICOMPETITIVE
FASHION.
ANTITRUST LAW HAS BEGUN TO HIT
ITS LIMITS WITH REGULATING TECH
COMPANIES.
IT WAS ALWAYS BASED AROUND THE
IDEA THAT THE REASON YOU GOT TO
STOP MONOPOLIES FROM HAPPENING
IS YOU GOT TO JACK UP PRICES.
THAT FRAME WORK MADE A LOT OF
SENSE THAT RAILROADS  KAEBT ABU
THE SYSTEM.
THE PRODUCT IS MADE FREE, OR AT
LEAST IT'S FREE ON ITS FACE.
WE'VE LEARNED IN PART BECAUSE OF
THE WAY OUR DATA ARE USED BY
THESE COMPANIES, THAT NOTHING IS
ACTUALLY FREE.
SO WEIR ARGOING TO NEED EMPOWER
THE FTC TO INTERVENE, INCLUDING
BLOCKING MERGERS WHERE THERE'S
ANTICOMPETITIVE BEHAVIOR BY TECH
COMPANIES, EVEN IF IT CAN'T
DIRECTLY BE APPLIED TO PRICING
BECAUSE YOUR NOT SEEING IT
BECAUSE IT'S FREE.
>> A SOPHOMORE STUDYING SOCIALGY
AND CHEMISTRY.
>> THERE ARE ABOUT 1100 OTHERS
THAT ARE NOT ADDRESSED.
HOW DO YOU ASS A
COMPREHENSIVE IMMIGRATION
REFORM?
>> I THINK REASON THE DREAMER
STORY IS SO POWERFUL IS IT
REFLECTS THE EXPERIENCES OF
PEOPLE WHO ARE AMERICANS.
THEY'RE NOT U.S. CITIZENS BUT IN
MANY CASES THIS A IS THE ONLY
COUNTRY THEY CAN EVEN REMEMBER
BECAUSE THEY CAME HERE THROUGH
NO CHOICE OF THEIR OWN AND IT'S
ONE OF THE REASONS WHY THERE'S A
BROAD U.S. CONSENSUS THAT WE
NEED FIND A WAY TO PROTECT
DREAMSERS.
THERE ARE OVER 10 MILLION PEOPLE
WHO ARE UNDOCUMENTED IMMIGRANTS
IN THIS COUNTRY WHO DON'T FALL
INTO THAT CATEGORY.
THE REALITY IS WE CAN'T HAVE
COMPREHENSIVE IMMIGRATION REFORM
THAT WIRKS UNLESS IT ADDRESSES
THE STATUS FOR THOSE 11 SOME
MILLION UNDOCUMENTED IMMIGRANTS.
WE NEED MAKE SURE THERE'S A
PATHWAY TO CITIZENSHIP FOR THEM
TOO.
THERE'S ACTUALLY AN AMERICAN
CONSENSUS OF WHAT WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO DO.
READERSHIP IS SUPPOSED TO BE
ABOUT TAKING ISSUES THAT ARE
DIVISIVE.
BUT RIGHT NOW WE HAVE AN ISSUE
WHERE THERE'S A PRETTY BROAD
CONSENSUS AND IT'S BEEN USED TO
DIVIDE US.
IT'S A REMARKABLE FEET OF
WHATEVER THE OPPOSITE OF
LEADERSHIP IS.
AND YOU CAN SEE IT BECAUSE THERE
HAVE BEEN HEALTHY COMPROMISES,
BIPARTISAN IMMIGRATION REFORM
THAT HAVE PASSED IN ONE CHAMBER
IN WASHINGTON, OWN 3 DIE IN THE
OTHERS.
THE LAST TIME WE EHAD A FULL,
MEANINGFUL COMPREHENSIVE REFORM
WAS 1984 AUTHORED BY RON IZOLI
AND BACK WHEN I WAS AN UNDERGRAD
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT HOW HAS IT
BEEN THIS LONG?
AND NOW IT'S BEEN JUST AS LONG
OR ALMOST SINCE THEN.
WE KNOW THE OUTLINES.
A PATHWAY TO CITIZENSHIP FOR
UNDOCUMENTED PEOPLE IN THIS
COUNTRY.
A LEVEL OF PROTECTION FOR
DREAMERS.
A SET OF REFORMS TO CLEAR UP THE
BUREAUCRACY AND THE BACK LOGS IN
THE LAWFUL IMMIGRATION SYSTEM,
WHICH IS HOW MY FATHER CAME TO
THE COUNTRY AND BECAME A U.S.
CITIZEN AND REASONABLE MEASURES
ON BORDER SECURITY.
WE KNOW WHAT TO DO.
IT'S JUST THAT WE DON'T HAVE THE
LEADERSHIP IN WASHINGTON TO DO
IT.
AND I'M AFRAID ONE OF THE
REASONS IS WE VEA WHITE HOUSE
THAT'S COMPUTED IT'S BETTER OFF
POLITICALLY THAT AMERICANS
CONTINUE TO BE DIVIDED A IT
FOR BCBC POLITICAL GAIN
AND THAT HAS GOT TO END WITH A
NEW PRESIDENT.
♪
>>> IF INDIANA ALLOWED IT, WOULD
YOU SUPPORT SOUTH BEND BEING A
SANCTUARY CITY?
>> ONE OF THE THINGS YOV RR
NOTICED BECAUSE WE WERE TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT THIS MEANT
WHEN THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE
WAS THREATENING MAYORS WITH
DRAWING OUR GRANT AND JAG FUNDS
FOR THE POLICE EDEPARTMENT BASED
ON WHETHER WE WERE A SANCTUARY
CITY.
THEY COULDN'T TELL US WHAT THAT
MEANS.
ER I REGAD US AS A WELCOMING
CITY.
ER SOME CONSERVATIVE TALK SHOW
HOST MAY SAY THAT MAKES US A
SANCTUARY CITY.
WE MAKE IT VERY CLEAR OUR SOUTH
BEND POLICE DEPARTMENT IS NOT
RESPONSIBLE FOR ENFORCING
IMMIGRATION POLICY.
MORE THAN A ENOUGH TO WORRY
ABOUT AND IT'S HARDER FOR THEM
TO DO THEIR JOB IF RESIDENTS,
MANY OF WHOM ARE IMMIGRANTS, AND
SOME UNDOCUMENTED, ARE AFRAID TO
TALK TO THEM, EVEN IF THEY KNOW
SOMETHINGX THAT MIGHT HELP THEM
ADDRESS A CRIME BECAUSE THEY'VE
BEEN LED TO BELIEVE THAT OUR
LO
LOCLAW ENFORCEMENT ARE BEING
CONSTRICTED SOMEHOW INTO DOING
THE JOB OF FEDERAL IMMIGRATION
AUTHORITIES.
THAT'S OUR POLICY.
WE'RE A WELCOMING CITY AND I
GUESS THE PRESIDENT THINKS
AMERICA IS FULL.
YEAR NOT.
I WOULD BE DELIGHTED TO HAVE
MORE PEOPLE.
WE ONLY HAVE 1HUNG,000 BECAUSE
SO MANY PEOPLE LEFT AFTER THE
AUTO COMPANIES COLLAPSED.
WE GOT PLENTY OF ROOM FOR
RESIDENTS AND TAXPAYERERS.
AND LET US NOT FORGET THAT IN
MANY RESPECTS FROM PROPERTY
TACKS TO SALES TAXES
UNDOCUMENTED IMMIGRANTS ARE
TAXPAYERERS AND THE TRUTH IS, IN
MANY RESPEKCTS, THEY'RE
SUBSIDIZING THE REST OF US.
WHICH IS ONE MORE REASON WE GOT
TO GET SORTED OUT.
>> YOU GOT ONE MORE QUESTION?
THIS IS A FRESHMAN FROM HARVARD.
>> PRETTY CLOSE TO SOUTH BEND.
I'M FROM SMALL MIDWESTERN TOWN
THAT'S BEEN EFFECTED BY THE POST
INDUSTRIAL SITUATION.
IN A INTERVIEW WITH DAVID
AXELROD, YOU NOTED NAFTA
RESULTED IN LOSSES ACROSS THE
MIDWEST.
HOW WOULD YOUR ADMINISTRATION
BRING SUCCESS?
>> IT'S CLOSE TO MY HEART
BECAUSE IT'S CLOSE TO MY HOME
TOWN.
AND DURING THE CHRYSLER PARTIAL
SHUTDOWN, WHAT WAS HAPPENING IN
AND AROUND HOWARD COUNTY WAS AN
EXAMPLE OF HOW VULNERABLE OUR
COMMUNITIES ARE TO OUR POLICIES
AND MARKETS WHEN IT COMES TO
MANUFACTURING.
SO WE NEED FIND A WAY TO MAKE
SURE TRADE WORKS FOR US.
THERE'S NO BUILDING A WALL
AROUND THE STATUS QUO.
DOESN'T WORK THAT WAY.
BUT WHAT WE DO NEED TO MAKE SURE
OF IS IT THERE'S ENOUGH MESHES
INCLUDING ADJUSTMENT ASSISTANCE,
INCLUDING MAKING SURE WE MAKE
WHOLE IN SOME WAY, THAT WE'RE
ACTUALLY KEEPING THE PROMISE OF
TRADE.
THE PROMISE MADE WHEN I WAS
GROWING UP IS IF WE DID THESE
THINGS, THE RISING TIDE WOULD
LIFT ANDL BE BETTER
OFF.
THE RISING TIDE ROSE.
IT'S JUST A LOT OF THE BOATS
TURNED OUT TO BE ANCHORERED TO
THE OCEAN FLOOR.
BUT WE CAN MAKE TRADE WORK FOR
OUR COMMUNITIES. UAW FACILITY IN
ST
ST. JOSEPHF COUNTY THAT IS
MAKING VEHICLES WHERE THE FUNDS
AND INVESTMENT CAME FROM CHINA
AND BEFORE THAT, THERE WAS A
THREE-YEAR CONTRACT WHERE THAT
FACILITY WAS WORKING FOR
MERCEDES AND THEY WERE MAKING
VEHICLES SOLD IN THE ASIAN
MARKET.
SO AMERICAN UNION OUGHT SO
WORKERS MAKING GERMAN CARS,
GOING TO CHINESE CUSTOMERS AND
WE'RE SENDING OUR -- NOT OUR
JOBS.
IN MAKING SURE WE HAVE FAIR
TRADE THAT WORKS IN COMMUNITIES
LIKE WHERE WE COME FROM, FOR
EVERY JOB TATS ARER BEEN LOST AS
A CONSEQUENCE OF TRADE THERE,
ARE SEVERAL MORE THAT HAVE BEEN
LOST AS A RESULT OF TECHNOLOGY
AND AUTOMATION.
THAT FACILITY MAKING ELECTRIC
VEHICLES, EVEN THOUGH THEY ARE
PLANNING TO MAKE SOMETHING LIKE
30ER TO 50,000 CARS, DOES IT
WITH HUNDREDS, NOT THOUSANDS OR
10S OF THOUSANDS THE WAY IT USED
TO WORK WHEN SOUTH BEND WAS AN
AUTOMOTIVE CENTER.
SO MANUFACTURING CAN CONTINUE TO
GROW STRONGER IN THIS COUNTRY.
BUT IT'S GOING TO BE LESS AND
LESS LABOR, LESS AND LESS HUMAN
BEING ON THE FLOOR.
AND THAT'S WHY WE NEED POLICIES
THAT CAN GET AHEAD OF THE
ECONOMIC SHIFTS TO COME AND
RECOGNIZE OUR GENERATION'S NOT
GOING TO BE ABLE TO COUNT AS OUR
PARENT'S GENERATION OFTEN DID ON
THE IDEA OF A SINGLE
RELATIONSHIP OR A COUPLE
EMPLOYERS ACROSS THE COURSE OF
OF YOUR CAREER.
>> KELSEY.
>> HI, MAYOR.
THE SCHOOL I ATTEND, UNIVERSITY
OF NEW HAMPSHIRE, HAS ONE OF THE
HIGHEST IN-STATE TUITION RATES
FOR THE WHOLE COUNTRY.
HOW WOULD YOU WORK TO MAKE THE
SO FUTURE STUDENTS WON'T HAVE TO
DEAL WITH SUCH A FINANCIAL
BURDEN?
>> THIS IS A PERSONAL ISSUE FOR
US BECAUSE WE LIVE WITH
SIX-FIGURE STUDENT DEBT.
IN PARTICULAR IN SPEAKING WITH
STUDENTS AND POLICY MAKERS IN
NEW HAMPSHIRE, I'VE LEARNED TO
THE EXTENT THAT IN-STATE TUITION
IS HIGHER THAN IT WOULD BE TO GO
OUT OF STATE TO A LOT OF OTHER
STATES, WHICH DEFEATS SO MUCH OF
OF THE PURPOSE OF HAVING
INSTITUTIONS THAT THERE SUPPOSED
TO BUILD UP THE LIFE OF OUR
STATE.
MAKES IT THAT MUCH HARDER IF
YOU'RE COMMITTED TO BEING PART
OF THE COMMUNITY.
ONE IN THE QUESTION THAT YOU
RAISED IS THROUGH A COMBINATION
OF CARROTS AND STICKS, WE'VE GOT
TO INDUCE STATES TO CARRY MORE
OF THE BURDEN, RATHER THAN PASS
IT ON TO STUDENTS.
STUDENTS ARE GETTING SQUEEZED
BECAUSE STATES ARE LESS AND LESS
WILLING TO MAKE SURE IT'S TRULY
AFFORDABLE.
ON THE BACK END WE'VE GOT TO
WORK ON STUDENT LOAN DEBT.
IF I CAN REFINANCE -- WHEN RATES
CHANGE, I CAN REFINANCE IT THE
LOAN ON MY HOUSE.
IT STANDS TO REASON THAT WE
SHOULD DO THAT WITH STUDENT DEBT
TOO.
COUPLED WITH A SIGNIFICANT
INCREASE IN PELGRANTS.
AND THIS TIME LET'S PEG IT
AUTOMATICALLY TO INFLATION SO WE
DON'T HAVE TO ASK CONGRESS TO DO
THAT AGAIN AND AGAIN.
>> ELIZABETH WARREN RELEASED A
PLAN THAT WOULD GIVE LOAN
RETLEEF HOUSEHOLDS WITH 50,000
LOAN CANCELLATIONS FOR FAMILIES
EARNING LESS THAN 100,000 DLF.
SHE SAYS IT WOULD COME FROM A
2% TAX OF --
>> I STILL WANT TO DO MATH
AROUND IT.
I FIND IT PRETTY APPEALING.
I'M NOT AS CERTAIN I'M
COMFORTABLE WITH PEOPLE THAT
HIGH OF AN INCOME PARTICIPATING
UNTIL WE HAVE A MORE PROGRESSIVE
TAX CODE BECAUSE I NING YOU'RE
NORTH OF $200,000, MAYBE YOU'RE
TO THE POINT WE CAN ASK YOU TO
TAKE CARE OF THE IT YOURSELF
BEUTTHE THEORY OF IT MAKES
SENSE.
>> WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A BREAK.
>> TECH: At Safelite AutoGlass,
we really pride ourselves
on making it easy
to get your windshield fixed.
>> TEACHER: Let's turn in your
science papers.
>> TECH VO: This teacher always
puts her students first.
>> STUDENT: I did mine
on volcanoes.
>> TEACHER: You did?! Oh, I
can't wait to read it.
>> TECH VO: So when she had
auto glass damage...
she chose Safelite.
With Safelite, she could see
exactly when we'd be there.
>> TEACHER: You must be Pascal.
>> TECH: Yes ma'am.
>> TECH VO: Saving her time...
[HONK, HONK]
>> KIDS: Bye!
>> TECH VO: ...so she can save
the science project.
>> KIDS: Whoa!
>> KIDS VO: ♪ Safelite repair,
Safelite replace ♪
♪♪
Every day,
visionaries are creating
the future.
♪♪
So, every day,
we put our latest technology
and unrivaled network to work.
♪♪
The United States
Postal Service makes
more e-commerce
deliveries to homes
than anyone else
in the country.
♪♪
Because the future only
happens with people
who really know how
to deliver it.
Because the future only
happens with people
♪♪
Applebee's Bigger, Bolder
Grill Combos.
Now that's Eatin Good
in the Neighborhood.
So, you're open all day,
every day.
That's what 24/7 means, sugar.
Kind of like how you
get 24/7 access
to licensed agents with GEICO.
Hmm?
Yeah, you just go online,
or give them a call anytime.
You don't say.
Yep. Now what will it take
to get 24/7 access
to that lemon meringue pie?
PIE!
PIE'S COMING!
That's what it takes, baby.
GEICO®. Great service
from licensed agents, 24/7.
>>> HERE WITH A SPECIAL CNN
DEMOCRATIC TOWN HALL EVENT.
WE'RE HERE WITH MAYORER PETE
BUTTIGIEG.
WE JUST CHECKED.
THE POLICY PORTAL IS ONLINE
SHOWING THE VIDEOS.
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS BUT I WANTED
TO MAKE SURE I WASN'T SAYING SO
ON TELEVISION.
>> YOU SAID AND I'M PARAPHRASING
THAT ANGER AND DISSATISFACTION
CAN LEAD THEM TO VOTE TO BLOW UP
THE SYSTEM WHICH CAN LEAD TO
SOMEBODY LIKE BERNIE SANDERS OR
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THERE WERER A LOT OF HEADLINES
AFTER THAT SAYING YOU WERE
COMPARING BERNIE SANDERS TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP?
>> I REGARD THEM AS STUPENDOUSLY
DIFFERENT IN MANY RESPECTS.
BUT I THINK IT'S WORTH NOTING
THERE IS SO MUCH
ANTIESTABLISHMENT ENERGY AND
THAT CAN FIND ITS WAY IN
DIFFERENT POLITICAL DIRECTIONS.
WHEN YOU THING OF OF THE NUMBER
OF VOTERS WHO NARROWED DOWN
THEIR CHOICES IN THE LAST
ELECTION, EITHER TO BERNIE
SANDERS OR DONALD TRUMP, IT
TELLS YOU SOME OF THE MOST
IMPORTANT THINGS ON VOTER'S
MINDS AREN'T JUST ARE YOU CLOSE
TO ME ON A LEFT/RIGHT POLITICAL
SPECTRUM?
BUT ARE YOU GOING TO PROFOUNDLY
CHANGING THE SYSTEM YEAR LIVING
IN?
AND THE PRESIDENT, IT WAS ALL
UNTRUE.
>> YOU CAN SAY PRETTY MUCH
ANYTHING ON CABLE.
>> WELL, IT'S BULL.
THERE WAS A SENSE I'M GOING TO
BLOW UP THE SYSTEM.
I THINK THIS IS IMPORTANT TO
UNDERSTAND BECAUSE WE NEED TO
MAKE SURE WE, STRATEGICALLY AS A
PARTY,ER THAT WE DON'T COME TO
BE VIEWED AS DEFENDERS OOF THE
SYSTEM THAT IS LETTING PEOPLE
DOWN AND WE WOULDN'T BE NEAR THE
ECONOMIC AND POLITICAL SYSTEM
HADN'T FAILED PEOPLE.
AND THIS IS NOT JUST IN THE
UNITED STATES BUT IN GENERAL.
PEOPLE ARE MORE SUSCEPTIBLE TO
MESSAGES AROUND HATE,
XENOPHOBIA, RACISM.
WHEN THEY FEEL OUT OF TOUCH WITH
POLITICAL ENVIRONMENT THEY'RE IN
OVERALL.
AND WE BETTER PAY ATTENTION
BECAUSE AS SOMEBODY WHO STUDIED
COUNTERRADICALIZATION ABROAD,
SOME OF THE SUPPORTS OF THIS
PRESIDENT ARE ADOPTING MORE AND
MORE EXTREME POSITIONS AND AS
MAINSTREAM REPUBLICANS START
LOOKING FOR SOME WAY OUT, IT
GIVES YOU ALMOST NOWHERE TEELS
GO.
IF SOMEBODY'S VOTED DEMOCRAT
AGAIN AND AGAIN RIGHT UP UNTIL
2016 AND THEN VOTED FOR TRUMP, I
WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT VOTER
STARTS VOTING DEMOCRATIC.
WE CAN'T JUST NIBBLE AROUND THE
EDGES AND EXPECT PEOPLE TO BE
HAPPY.
I HAVE A SLIGHTLY DIFFERENT
ACCOUNT THAN MY COMPETITORS.
BUT THE LESSON IS IT'S BEEN
LETTING PEOPLE DOWN, I WOULD SAY
FOR MY ENTIRE LIFETIME.
AND ONE OF THE REASONS WE'RE AT
THIS TECTONIC MOMENT A ONCE IN
EVERY HALF CENTURY OR SO MOMENT
THERE'S A HINGE POINT BETWEEN
ERAS IN AMERICAN HISTORY.
AS BIG AS THE MOMENT WHEN THE
NEW DEAL CAME ABOUT OR THE ONE
WE'VE BEEN LIVING THROUGH EVER
SINCE EWHEN REGANISM BECAME
ASCENDANT IN THIS COUNTRY.
THAT'S COME TO AN END AND WE'RE
AT THE DAWN OF SOMETHING NEW AND
IT COULD BE ENLIGHTENED
FANTASTIC OR CAN BE UGLY.
AND AS MUCH AS I CARE ABOUT
REPLACING THIS PRESIDENT AND
WINNING THIS ELECTION, WHALT'S T
STAKE IS NOT JUST WINNING AN
ELECTION BUT AN ERA.
>> BERNIE SANDERS SAID HE'S IN
FAVOR OF FELONS BEING ABLE TO
VOTE, EVEN WHILE SERVING THEIR
TERMS.
AND PEOPLE PED FILES -- HE SAID
IT'S INHERENT TO THE RIGHT FOR
DEMOCRACY, YES, FOR ALL PEOPLE.
SHTD PEOPLE CONVICTED OF SEXUAL
ASSAULT, SHOULD THEY BE ABLE TO
■TED?
>> YES.
>> NO.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I DO BELIEVE THAT WHEN YOU HAVE
SERVED YOUR SENTENCE, THEN PART
OF BEING RESTORED TO SOCIETY IS
THAT YOU ARE PART OF THE
POLITICAL LIFE OF THIS NATION
AGAIN AND ONE OF THE THINGS THAT
NEEDS TO BE RESTORED IS YOUR
RIGHT TO VOTE.
AS YOU KNOW SOME STATES AND
COMMUNITIES TO DO IT.
I THINK WE WOULD BE A BETTER
COUNTRY EIF EVERYBODY DID IT AND
I THINK THE MOTIVATIONS FOR
PREVENTING THAT IN SOME CASES
HAVE TO DO WITH ONE SIDE OF THE
AISLE NOTICING THEY POLITICALLY
BENEFIT AND THAT'S GOT RACIAL
LAYERS TO IT.
PART OF THE PUNISHMENT WHEN YOU
WERE CONVICTED OFF A CRIME AND
YOU'RE INCARCERATED IS YOU LOSE
CERTAIN RIGHTS.
YOU LOSE YOUR FREEDOM AND I
THINK DURING THAT FREEDOM IT
DOES NOT MAKE SENSE TO HAVE AN
EXCEPTION FOR IT THE RIGHT TO
VOTE.
>> WE HAVE A QUESTION FROM --
[ APPLAUSE ]
WE HAVE A QUESTION FROM EMILY
BROTHER.
SHE'S A SENIOR STUDYING MUSIC.
>> THANK YOU FOR TAKING MY
QUESTION.
IN YOUR ■AUTOBIOGRAPHY "SHORTES
WAY EHOME" YOU WERE PROUD OF
SETTING AND ACHIEVING THE GOAL
OF 1,000 VACANT OR ABANDONED
HOUSES BULLDOZED.
CAN YOU OFFER INSIGHT INTO WHAT
YOU'VE SINCE LEARNED FROM THE
RAMIFICATIONS AND CRITICISMS OF
THIS PROJECT AND HOW THIS WOULD
FORM YOU IN CRAFTING
LEGISLATION?
>> LET ME EXPLAIN HOW WE GOT TO
THAT POINT.
SOUTH BEND LOST ABOUT 30,000
PEOPLE BETWEEN THE 1960s IN THE
IT TIME I WAS RUNNING FOR MAYOR.
ESPECIALLY WHEN I WAS KNOCKING
ON DOORS IN MINORITY AND LOW
INCOME NEIGHBORHOODS.
I ALSO ASKED A LOT OF QUESTIONS
ABOUT WHAT WAS GOING ON AND WHAT
IS IT THE BIGGEST THING YOU WISH
THE IT CITY WAS DOING FOR YOU?
AND THE NUMBER ONE ANSWERER I
HEARD CITY WIDE BUT AN ANSWER I
HEARD IN PARTICULAR FROM PEOPLE
LIVING IN MINORITY AND LOW
EINCOME NEIGHBORHOODS WAS DO
SOMETHING ABOUT THE VACANT,
BOARDED UP AND COLLAPSING HOUSES
AROUND ME BECAUSE IF YOU'RE A
HOME OWNER AND THERE WERE SO
MANY HOME OWNERS, ESPECIALLY IN
AREAS THAT HAVE BEEN VICTIMIZED
AND CRANICALLY LOW EINCOME, IT
DESTROYED THE VALUE ALSO.
IF YOU'RE NOT A HOME OWN, A
RENTER, THEN YOU'RE LIVING IN A
HOME WHERE AN ABANDONED HOME
COULD BE USED FOR
HEADQUARTERERS.
AND SO I ASKED HOW MANY EHOUSES
DO WE HAVE TO DEAL WITH AND
NOBODY COULD TELL US.
AND SO THAT'S WHEN WE STARTED
ABOUT YEAR-LONG PROCESS OF
TRYING TO MAP THE ISSUE.
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A HOUSE
THAT'S AN ISOLATED CASE IN A
RELATIVELY WELL-OFF
NEIGHBORHOOD, WHICH MEANT IT WAS
THE CASE THAT THE BEST APPROACH
WAS PROBABLY JUST AGGRESSIVE
CODE ENFORCEMENT BECAUSE CHANCES
ARE THE OWNER HAD IT THE MEANS
TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT OR MORE
THAN 50% OF THE HOMES VACANT.
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE ONE OF THE
THINGS WE WERE FINDING WAS A LOT
OF THE LAND OWNERS HAD WALKED
AWAY THRUM HOUSES YEARS AGO OR
CLEVERLY FIGURED OUT WAYS TO
DISGUISE WHO OWNED THE HOUSE.
WE'D LOOK UP WHO OWNED IT SO WE
COULD HOLD THEM ACCOUNTABLE.
THERE'S NO WAY TO HAVE
ACCOUNTABILITY.
AND I THOUGHT THESE
NEIGHBORHOODS ARE NEVER GOING TO
BE AS SAFE AS WE WANT THEM TO BE
UNLESS WE DO SOMETHING AND ACT
FAST.
THAT'S WHY WE SET ASIDE FUNDING
TO REINVEST IT IT IN THE FORM OF
REPAIRS ON HOUSES, DEMOLISHING
HOUSES WE COULDN'T AND
ENFORCEMENT FOR IRRESPONSIBLE
LANDLORDS THAT WERE ALLOWING
THESE HOMES TO DETERIORATE.
NO POLICY IS PERFECT AND WE
LEARNED THINGS THE HARD WAY ON
THIS ONE.
OUR POLICY TOOLS DIDN'T DO A
GREAT JOB AT FIRST OF BEING ABLE
TO TELL THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A
BIG, BAD, OUT OF TOWN HOME OWNER
AND SOMEBODY WHO MAYBE HAD THREE
OR FOURER PROPERTIES OR SOMEBODY
WOULD BUY A HOUSE AND NOT EVEN
KNOW IT WAS ON THE VACANT AND
ABANDONED LIST AND THAT WE WERE
COMING TO DEMOLISH IT.
OVER TIME WE LEARNED TO BE MORE
IN DIALOGUE WITH HOME OWNERS OR
A MORE ACCOMMODATING
CONVERSATION BETWEEN THE HOME
OWNERSHIP SIDE.
WE LEARNED THE VALUE OF
COMMUNICATION.
QUANTITY/TIME.
AND IT'S STILL AN EFFORT SOME
PEOPLE HAD FRUSTRATIONS WITH.
BUT THE NUMBER ONE CAN COMPLAINT
WE HEARD, ESPECIALLY FROM
MINORITY AND LOW INCOME HOME
OWNERS IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD WAS
WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
>> ANOTHER QUESTION FROM LONDON
VALLEY.
BUT FIRST I NEED TO GIVE YOU
BACKGROUND.
IN 2012 IT WAS DISCOVERED THE
POLICE CHIEF OF SOUTH BEND HAD
BEEN TAPING PHONE CONVERSATIONS
OF SENIOR POLICE OFFICERS
ALLEGEDLY USING RACIST LANGUAGE
AND PARTICULARLY ABOUT HIM.
YOU DEMOTED THE POLICE CHIEF.
NO ACTION WAS TAKEN AGAINST THE
OFFICERS.
>> MAYOR, MY QUESTION IS
STRAIGHT FORWARD.
WHAT ARE ON THE SECRET TAPES
REGARDING THE FLAT PIECE CHIEF?
>> SO THE ANSWER IS I DON'T
KNOW.
AND THE REASON I DON'T KNOW IS
THESE TAPE RECORDINGS WERE MADE
IN A WAY THAT SPLA VIOLATED THE
FEDERAL WIRE TAP ACT.
IT CONTROLS WHEN YOU CAN AND
CAN'T RECORD PEOPLE.
AND THE ALLEGATION WAS THE IT
POLICE CHIEF WAS USING THESE
RECORDING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT WAS
GOING ON WITH INTERNAL RIVALRIES
AND ALLEGEDLY BROKE THE FEDERAL
WIRE TAP ACT WHEN HE DID THAT.
THAT'S A LAW PUNISHABLE BY A
TERM IN PRISON AND SO I'M NOT
GOING TO VIOLATE IT, EVEN THOUGH
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON
THE TAPES LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE
DOES.
AND THE JUDGE TO SAY WHETHER OR
NOT THE CONTENT OF THE
RECORDINGS TO BE RELEASED.
THE REASON I DEMOTED THE CHIEF
WAS THE SUBJECT OF A CRIMINAL
INVESTIGATION AND IT MADE IT
VERY PAINFUL TOO HE'S THE FIRST
AFRICAN-AMERICAN CHIEF AND ONE
OF THE REASONS I ASKED HIM TO
SERVE IN THE FIRST PLACE WAS A
GREAT TRACK RECORD IN COMMUNITY
POLICING, WHICH IS A HUGE
PRIORITY FOR US BECAUSE WE'RE A
RACIALLY DIVERSE COMMUNITY AND
SPEAKING OF THINGS YOU LEARN
ALONG THE WAY.
ONE OF THE THINGS I REALIZED IS
WHILE I WAS ABSORBED IN MAKING
SURE WE WEREN'T TRIPPING ON ANY
LAND LINES RELATED TO LAWS OF
WHAT YOU CAN AND CAN'T RECORD, I
WAS FRANKLY A LITTLE SLOW TO
UNDERSTAND JUST HOW MUCH ANGUISH
UNDERTHEY ARE COMMUNITY'S
RESPONSE.
BECAUSE IT WASN'T JUST ABOUT
WHETHER WE WERE RIGHT OR WRONG
TO BE CONCERNED ABOUT THE
FEDERAL WIRE TAP ACT, IT WAS
ABOUT WHETHER COMMUNITIES OF
COLOR COULD TRUST THAT
COMMUNITIES HAD THEIR BEST
INTERESTEST AT HEART.
THE MORE I REALIZED LIFTING THE
VEIL OF MISTRUST BETWEEN
COMMUNITIES OF COLOR AND OUR
POLICE DEPARTMENT HAD TO BE ONE
OF MY TOP PRIORITIES AS MAYOR.
IT'S WHY WE IMPLEMENTED BODY
WORN CAMERAS FOR ALL OF OUR
OFFICERS AND GET TO KNOW PEOPLE
IN THESE NEIGHBORHOODS,
ESPECIALLY EXPERIENCING A LOT OF
CRIME, NOT IN AN ENFORCEMENT
ENVIRONMENT, BUT A TRUST BUILD
NOTHING ENVIRONMENT.
AND A NUMBER OF OTHER MEASURES
INCLUDING MORE MINORITY RECRUITS
IN THE DEPARTMENT ITSELF.
SO THERE'S MORE OF THAT TRUST.
>> RIGHT NOW THE IT POLICE FORCE
WAS 5% AFRICAN-AMERICAN.
AND THE TWO POLICE CHIEFS YOU
HIRED SUBSEQUENTLY WERE BOTH
WHITE.
>> ONE OF THE THINGS WE DID ALSO
AS A RESPONSE TO LEARNING HOW
MUCH RESPONSE IN THE COMMUNITY
WAS LEARNING A
COMMUNITY-ORIENTED PROCESS.
AND I BELIEVE WE WOULD NOT HAVE
BEEN ABLE TO MAKE THOSE
IMPROVEMENTS WITHOUT HAVING VERY
QUALIFIED GOOD PEOPLE COME ON
BOARD.
BUT THESE ARE THE CHALLENGES,
WHETHER IT'S THE RELATIONSHIP OF
COMMUNITIES OF COLORER TO POLICE
DEPARTMENTS OR HOMELESSNESS,
HOUSING, POVERTY.
AND FRANKLY, THEY'RE NOT
PROBLEMS YOU SOLVE OVERNIGHT BUT
I BELIEVE THEY ARER PROBLEMS
THAT PEOPLE WITH GOOD WILL AND A
LISTENING HEARTER ARE ABLE TO
MAKE PROGRESS ON AND I IT DON'T
THINK I WOULD HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
BE REELECTED INCLUDING WINNING
MINORITY DISTRICTS IN OUR CITY
IF IT WEREN'T FOR THE VERY HARD
WORK WE DID IN THE YEARS SINCE
THAT INCIDENT REALLY THREATENED
TO TEAR OUR CITY APART TO TRY TO
HEAL.
ES FOR AND I DON'T CLAIM WE GOT
EVERY STEP PERFECT.
BUT I WILL TELL YOU I DID
EVERYTHING BASED ON THE BEST
JUDGMENT AND DESIRE TO DO WHAT'S
GOOD FOR OUR COMMUNITY.
AND I BELIEVE WE NEED THAT KIND
OF OF ATTENTION AND WILLINGNESS
TO ADJUST.
WE NEED A LOT MORE OF THAT IN
WASHINGTON, ESPECIALLY IN THE
WHITE HOUSE.
>> ONE OF THE THINGS -- YOU KNOW
WE HAVE A LOT OF FOLKS FROM
HARVARDEREDER.
THEY HAVE A YOUTH POLL OUT.
H
HYMEN -- HUMAN ROIGTSZ IS A TOP
PRIORITY FOR VOTERS.
ER.
>> RIGHT.
WELCOME BACK TO NEW HAMPSHIRE.
MY QUESTION IS HOW WOULD YOU
COOP WRAT COUNTRIES THAT VIEW
HOM
HOME SEXUALITY AS A CRIME TATS
ARER PUNISHABLE BY DEATH?
>> WELL, I THINK IT'S WRONG TO
HARM OR PUNISH PEOPLE BECAUSE
THEY'RE PART OF THE LGBTQ
COMMUNITY.
I SKBHOE AREN'T THERE.
IN SOME RESPECTS OUR OWN COUNTRY
ISN'T THERE.
IT THIS IS WHY THE WORLD NEEDS
AN AMERICA THAT'S STRONG AND
CREDIBLE AND PEOPLE BELIEVE
KEEPS ITS WORD.
THE ABILITY OF OF THE NEXT
PRESIDENT AND THE U.S. IN
GENERAL TO LEAD ON THIS ISSUE
AND GUIDE COUNTRIES TOWARDS THE
RIGHT THING, DOES ANYBODY
BELIEVE THEY HAVE MORAL
AUTHORITY IN THE WORLD?
IT'S PLUMMETED AND FRANKLY ANY
KIND OF HUMAN RIGHTS OR
DEMOCRACY PROMOTION WE WANT TO
ADVANCE, EITHER BECAUSE WE THINK
IT MAKES SENSE FROM AN AMERICAN
PERSPECTIVE OR BECAUSE WE THINK
IT'S CONSISTENT WITH AN
ASPERATION FOR A BETTER LIFE.
I STILL BELIEVE IN THE AMERICAN
MODEL FOR ALL ITS FLAWS.
WHEN I LOOK ON THE THE WORLD
STAGE I THINK IT THE AMERICAN
WAY OF DOING THINGS, OUR EFFORTS
HOWEVER IMPERFECT ESTABLISH THE
RIGHT WAY TO GO AND THERE'S A
LOT OF OTHER MODELS BEING HELD
UP AS CREDIBLE ALTERNATIVES.
THE CHINESE MODEL.
AUTHORITARIANISM IS BEING HELD
UP AGAINST THE CHAOS AND
DIVISION OF AMERICA RIGHT NOW.
IT'S BEING HELD UP AS AN
ALTERNATIVE.
THE RUSSIAN MODEL IS THROWING
ITS WEIGHT AROUND.
DON'T GET ME START ODON THE
SAUDI MODEL.
THERE ARE OUGHT LOT OF OTHER
WAYS COUNTRIES CAN OPERATE.
AND BENEFIT AMONG OTHER THINGS
VARIOUS MINORITIES BUT NOT IF
WE'RE NOT CREDIBLE.
AND WE'VE GOT TO DO BETTER ON
THAT AND THE NEXT PRESIDENT
PROBABLY WILL MAKE ALL THE
DIFFERENCE IN THIS INCREDEBLE
SENSITIVE TIME OF WORLD AFFAIRS.
WHETHER WE GET INTO THE 20th
CENTURY OR SOMETHING PEOPLE
SCRATCH THEIR HEADS ABOUT.
>> I WANT TO ASK YOU A PERSONAL
QUESTION IF I CAN.
WHEN YOU CAME OUT PUBLICLY 2013.
HOW DO YOU THINK YOUR LIFE WOULD
BE DIFFERENT IF YOU CAME OUT
BEFORE THEN?
>> I CAME OUT BECAUSE I WANTED
TO DATE.
AND IF DATING HAD BEEN AVAILABLE
TO ME IN MY 20s, I'M NOT SURE I
WOULD HAVE GOT NEARLY AS MUCH
DONE.
HONESTLY I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY.
WHAT I DO KNOW IST FIRST I
CONVINCED MYSELF I DIDN'T NEED
MUCH ELSE I WAS ALSO A MEM BEOF
THE RESERVE.
AND THE CITY WAS A JEALOUS
BRIDE.
I WAS FINE WITH THAT UP TO A
POINT.
IT WAS WHEN I CAME BACK FROM MY
DEPLOYMENT AND I CAME BACK FROM
THAT LEAVE OF ABSENCE THAT I
STAED THINKING ABOUT HOW YOU
ONLY GET TO LIVE ONE LIFE.
AND I CAME OUT AND I STARTED
DATING AND I FOUND CHASTEN AND
EVEN THOUGH IN THE PAST I WAS
MYSTIFIED WITH THE IDEA OF HOW
ANY OFF MY FELLOW MAYORS OR
ELECTED OFFICIALS MANAGED TO DO
THAT JOB AND BE IN RELATIONSHIPS
AND BE MARRIED.
I DON'T KNOW HOW I DO THIS
WITHOUT HIM.
I GUESS TO ANSWERER YOUR
QUESTION I WOULD NOT BE RUNNING
FOR PRESIDENT TODAY IF I HAD NOT
COME OUT.
>> I WANT TO BRING IN --
ACTUALLY GOING TO TAKE A SHORTER
BREAK.
BRING BACK SOUTH BEND, INDIANA
MAYOR.
Shaving has been difficult for
me.
I have very sensitive skin, and
I get ingrowing hairs.
So it's a daunting task.
Oh I love it. It's a great
razor.
It has that 'fence' in the
middle.
It gives a nice smooth shave.
Just stopping that irritation...
That burn that I get is really
life changing.
The right gear...
matters.
Introducing the all-new
2019 Ford Ranger,
It's the right gear.
With a Terrain Management
System for... this.
A bash plate for... that.
An Electronic Locking Rear
Differential for...
Yeah... this.
Heading to the supermarket?
Get any truck.
Heading out here?
Get the Ford Ranger.
The only adventure gear
Built Ford Tough.
My name is Bailey
and this is Ethan.
Go!
That isn't getting
any easier.
This is CJ, the greatest
addition to our pack.
Doggie.
But I could tell my time
was coming to an end.
When you come back the
next time, take care of CJ.
I promise.
I was back and
I would be there for CJ.
I don't have all the
answers but I know
we end up where
we're meant to be.
Carl, I appreciate
the invite here.
As my broker,
what am I paying you
to manage my money?
It's racquetball time.
(Thumps)
Ugh!
Carl, does your firm offer
a Satisfaction Guarantee?
Like Schwab does.
Guarantee?
(Splash)
Carl, can you remind me
what you've invested
my money in?
It's complicated.
Are you asking enough questions
about the way your wealth
is being managed?
If not, talk to Schwab.
A modern approach to Wealth
Management.
>>> HEY, WELCOME BACK TO OUR
SPECIAL DEMOCRATIC TOWN HALL
EVENT.
Y
WE'RE IN THE HOMESTRETCH.
VERY QUICKLY.
IF YOU WERE IN THE HOUSE OR
SENATE, WOULD YOU STREET IMPEACH
PRESIDENT TRUMP?
DO YOU THINK THE HOUSE SHOULD
MOVE FOR IMPEACHMENT?
>> I THINK HE'S MADE IT PRETTY
CLEAR HE DESERVES IMPEACHMENT.
IAL ARE LEAVE IT TO THE -- I'M
ALSO GOING TO LEAVE IT TO THE
HOUSE AND SENATE TO FIGURE THAT
OUT.
MY JAB IS TO RELIGATE TRUMPISM
TO THE DUST BIN OF HISTORY.
AND HAVE AN ABSOLUTE THUMPING AT
IT THE BALLOT BOX.
FRERS
>> DO YOU THINK IF DEMOCRATS
FOCUS ON THIS IT'S GOING TO TAKE
AWAY --
>> CONGRESS IS GOING TO HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO DO SEVERAL
THINGS AT ONCE BUT WHILE WE'RE
FIGURING OUT OVERSIGHT, WHICH
WE'VE GOT TO BEX WE HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT THINGS THAT MOST
EFFECT PEOPLE IN AN IMMEDIATE
AND CONCRETE WAY.
A LOT OFF VOTERS ARE DISEFFECTED
ENTIRELY.
AND IF WE'RE ONLY TALKING ABOUT
HIM, AND FOLKS AT HOME FEEL LIKE
NOBODY IS TALKING ABOUT THEM.
IT'S HARD TO LOOK AWAY FROM HEIR
HORRORER SHOW.
IT'S MESMERIZING.
BUT WE'VE GOT TO FIGURE OUT A
WAY TO CHANGE THE CHANNEL.
>> HE'S A STUDENT AT HARVARD LAW
SCHOOL.
YIKES.
I'M A TOTAL SHRUB.
HE SERVED AS A SURFER'S WARFARE
OFFICER IN THE NAVY.
HE'S GOT EVERYTHING.
SHAWN HAS A QUESTION ABOUT YOUR
TIME IN THE IT NAVY RESERVES.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR SERVICE AND
FOR BEING HERE.
>> MAYOR BUTTIGIEG.
.
>> AS A NAVY VETERAN I WONDER
HOW YOU RECONCILE YOUR CRITICISM
OF PRESIDENT TRUMP WITH YOUR
ALLEGIANCE TO OUR COMMANDER IN
CHIEF.
HAVE YOU EVER HAD TO TEMPER WHAT
YOU SAY ABOUT THE PRESIDENT
BECAUSE OF YOUR AFFILIATION WITH
THE NAVY RESERVE.
>> FIRST OF ALL, THANKS FOR YOUR
SERVICE.
I THOUGHT ABOUT THIS A LOT WHEN
I WAS SERVING.
DURING THE TIME I WAS IN THE
RESERVE, I SEPARATED A COUPLE
YEARS AGO, I ALWAYS TRIED IN
PARTICULAR WHEN I WAS IN
UNIFORM, AT DRILL, OR WHEN I WAS
DEPLOYED TO KEEP MY POLITICS OUT
OF IT BECAUSE I THINK ALL OF US
ARRIVE WITH POLITICAL VIEWS.
NOW, THAT SAID, THE VERY THING
OR ONE OF THE THINGS I BELIEVE
THAT I WAS SERVING TO DEFEND
WITH MY LIFE WAS THE FACT THAT
WE'RE A COUNTRY WHERE YOU GET TO
BE CRITICAL OF YOUR POLITICAL
LEADERS.
I SWORE AN OATH TO THE
CONSTITUTION, NOT TO THE
PRESIDENT.
AND THAT'S WHERE OUR ULTIMATE
LOYALTY HAS TO LIE.
BUT THE OTHER THING THAT
HAPPENED WHILE I WAS SERVING
ABROAD WAS THAT I LEARNED TO
TRUST MY LIFE TO PEOPLE WHO HAD
TOTALLY DIFFERENT POLITICAL
VIEWS THAN I DID.
THAT WAS THE AMAZING THING, AS
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU SERVE, IT WAS
AN INSTITUTION THAT DREW PEOPLE
FROM ALL PARTS OF THE COUNTRY.
IT WAS THE MOST RACIALLY
INTEGRATED ORGANIZATION I'VE
EVER BEEN A PART OF AND THERE
WERE PEOPLE GETTING INTO MY
VEHICLE WHO WE COULDN'T AGREE ON
A SINGLE THING POLITICALLY.
SOME PEOPLE THAT THE ONLY THING
WE HAD IN COMMON WAS THE FACT OF
BEING AMERICAN.
AND YET KNOWING THAT WE HAD A
JOB TO DO WE LEARNED TO TRUST
EACH OTHER WITH OUR LIVES.
NOW, I BELIEVE YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE TO GO TO WAR IN ORDER TO
HAVE THAT KIND OF EXPERIENCE.
WHICH IS WHY I BELIEVE AMERICA
NEEDS TO CREATE MORE
OPPORTUNITIES FOR NATIONAL
SERVICE, IN PARTICULAR SERVICE
YEAR OPPORTUNITIES FOR PEOPLE
AFTER THEY FINISH HIGH SCHOOL SO
THAT IN ADDITION TO THE MILITARY
WE BUILD UP THINGS LIKE CITY
EARTH, AMERCORPS, OTHER WAYS TO
BE PART OF THAT FASHIONING A
COMMON CHARACTER AT THIS MOMENT
WHEN SOCIAL MEDIA AND OUR
DIFFERENT BUBBLES HAVE US
INCREASINGLY FLOATING IN OUR OWN
LITTLE PARTS OF THIS COUNTRY
WHEN FOR PRIOR GENERATIONS IT
WAS MILITARY SERVICE THAT GAVE
PEOPLE WITH RADICALLY DIFFERENT
BACKGROUNDS ALMOST AS A MATTER
OF COURSE WHEN IT WAS, FOR
EXAMPLE, PRETTY MUCH ASSUMED IF
YOU GRADUATED FROM AN IVY LEAGUE
INSTITUTION THAT YOU WOULD GO
INTO THE MILITARY.
A GOOD NATIONAL SERVICE PROGRAM
COULD HELP US DO JUST THAT.
>> OUR NEXT QUESTION COMES FROM
CAMILLE, A FRESHMAN FROM
HARVARD.
>> MAYOR BUTTIGIEG, YOU'VE
TALKED OPENLY ABOUT YOUR STRONG
CHRISTIAN MAN AS WELL AS YOUR
IDENTITY AS A GAY MARRIED MAN.
HOW WILL YOU UNITE THIS BEHIND
YOU AND YOUR PLATFORM?
>> IT CAN BE CHALLENGING TO BE A
PERSON OF THE FAITH WHO'S ALSO
PART OF THE LGBTQ COMMUNITY AND
YET TO ME THE CORE OF FAITH IS
REGARD FOR ONE ANOTHER.
AND PART OF HOW GOD'S LOVE IS
EXPERIENCEDING TO MY
FAITH TRADITION IS IN THE WAY
THAT WE SUPPORT ONE ANOTHER AND
IN PARTICULAR SUPPORT THE LEAST
AMONG US.
AGAIN, LET ME PREFACE THIS BY
SAYING I BELIEVE STRONGLY IN THE
SEPARATION OF CHURCH AND STATE
AND I THINK ANYBODY WHO STEPS
INTO THE PUBLIC SPHERE NEEDS TO
MAKE IT CLEAR THAT THEY'RE HERE
TO SUPPORT PEOPLE OF ANY
RELIGION AND PEOPLE OF NO
RELIGION.
BUT I ALSO THINK WE OUGHT TO BE
HONEST ABOUT WHERE WE'RE COMING
FROM.
PART OF WHERE I'M COMING FROM IS
A FAITH TRADITION THAT COUNSELS
ME TO BE AS HUMBLE AS POSSIBLE,
THAT COUNSELS ME TO LOOK AFTER
THOSE WHO NEED DEFENDING.
AND FRANKLY IT COULDN'T BE MORE
RADICALLY DIFFERENT THAN WHAT I
SEE CERTAINLY IN THIS WHITE
HOUSE WHERE THERE'S A LOT OF
CHEST THUMPING AND
SELF-AGGRANDIZING, NOT TO
MENTION ABUSIVE BEHAVIOR.
BUT ALSO A POLITICAL AGENDA THAT
SEEMS TO ALWAYS BE REVOLVING
AROUND THE IDEA THAT SOMEHOW
IT'S TOO EASY FOR POOR PEOPLE IN
THIS COUNTRY R IT'S JUST SO
DIFFERENT THAN WHAT I GET WHEN I
READ SCRIPTURE.
AND I GET THAT ONE OF THE THINGS
ABOUT SCRIPTURE IS DIFFERENT
PEOPLE SEE DIFFERENT THINGS IN
IT.
BUT AT THE VERY LEAST WE SHOULD
BE ABLE TO ESTABLISH THAT GOD
DOES NOT HAVE A POLITICAL PARTY.
>> JUST TO FOLLOW UP ON THAT,
YOU'VE GOTTEN INTO A PUBLIC BACK
AND FORTH BETWEEN VICE PRESIDENT
PENCE AND YOURSELF OVER THE
ISSUE OF DISCRIMMATION AGAINST
LGBTQ PEOPLE AND FAITH, THE
CURRENT AMBASSADOR SO GERMANY
WEIGHED IN ON THIS SAYING YOU
HAVE BEEN QUOTE PUSHING THIS
HATE HOAX ALONG THE LINES OF
JUSSIE SMOLLETT FOR A VERY LONG
TIME NOW, SEVERAL WEEKS.
HOW DO YOU RESPOND TO THAT?
>> I'M NOT A MASTER FISHERMAN,
BUT I KNOW BAIT WHEN I SEE IT
AND I'M NOT GOING TO TAKE IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
OUR NEXT QUESTION -- OUR NEXT
QUESTION COMES FROM -- OUR NEXT
QUESTION COMES FROM A GRADUATE
STUDENT AT THE HARVARD KENNEDY
SCHOOL FROM OREGON.
>> GOOD EVENING, MY QUESTION IS,
MANY PEOPLE ACCUSE OUR
GENERATION, I'M 31, AND YOUNGER
GENERATIONS OF BEING FAKE WOKE,
OR OF THE AGE OF INSTAGRAM.
AS THE YOUNGEST CANDIDATE WHAT
DO YOU THINK SETS YOU APART FROM
THE OTHER CANDIDATES AND WHAT DO
YOU THINK HAS BEEN UNFAIR
CRITICISM?
>> WELL, I THINK, YOU KNOW, IN
THE SAME WAY A CANDIDATE NEEDS
TO BE THERE FOR PEOPLE OF EVERY
RELIGION OR NO RELIGION YOU'VE
GOT TO BE THERE FOR PEOPLE OF
EVERY GENERATION.
THE LONGER YOU'RE PLANNING TO BE
HERE, BY DEFINITION, THE MORE
YOU HAVE AT STAKE IN THE
DECISIONS THAT ARE GOING TO BE
MADE, ESPECIALLY WHEN CLIMATE
CHANGE IS LARGELY GOING TO
DICTATE THE ECONOMIC
OPPORTUNITIES AND EVEN PHYSICAL
SAFETY OF PEOPLE OUR AGE AND
YOUNGER IN PARTICULAR.
AT A TIME WHEN WE'RE GOING TO BE
ASKED TO FOOT THE BILL FOR
UNAFFORDABLE TAX CUTS ON
BILLIONAIRES PASSED BY THE LAST
CONGRESS AND SIGNED BY THIS
ADMINISTRATION.
WHILE I THINK ANYBODY OF ANY AGE
CAN SPEAK TO THESE ISSUES I
THINK HAVING A PERSONAL STAKE IN
WHAT THE WORLD'S GOING TO LOOK
LIKE IN 2054, THAT'S THE YEAR I
GET TO THE CURRENT AGE OF THE
CURRENT PRESIDENT, I THINK
HAVING A PERSONAL STAKE IN THAT
HELPS YOU HAVE STANDING TO SPEAK
TO SOME OF THESE ISSUES AND
CONCERNS.
I DO THINK THAT SOMETIMES PEOPLE
LOOK AT OUR GENERATION AND RAISE
AN EYEBROW.
PART OF IT IS OUT OF A SENSE
THAT WE'RE NOT AS POLITICALLY
ENGAGED.
WHEN I WAS A STUDENT, AROUND THE
TIME THE IOP STARTED DOING AN
ANNUAL POLL, A BODY OF RESEARCH
AROUND YOUNG PEOPLE'S
INVOLVEMENT IN POLITICS AND THE
HYPOTHESIS THEY WERE TESTING AT
THE TIME WAS THE YOUNG PEOPLE
DON'T CARE AS MUCH, PATTERNS OF
VOTING AND VOLUNTEERISM WERE
LOW.
WHAT WE FOUND WAS THAT WHILE
VOTING AND VOLUNTEERISM ON
CAMPAIGNS WAS LOW, VOLUNTEERING
IN COMMUNITIES WAS HIGH.
THE QUESTION WASN'T WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOUNG PEOPLE, THE QUESTION
WAS, WHAT'S WRONG WITH OUR
SYSTEM, THE YOUNG PEOPLE WHO
CLEARLY DO CARE ABOUT THE WORLD
AROUND THEM DON'T NECESSARILY
BELIEVE THAT POLITICS HAS
ANYTHING TO OFFER THEM.
THAT'S SOMETHING WE'VE GOT TO I
THINK WHICH A.
WHILE I PASSIONATELY BELIEVE
THAT EVERY YOUNG PERSON OUGHT TO
BE INVOLVED, OUGHT TO VOTE,
OUGHT TO BE ENGAGED, OUGHT TO
HOLD CANDIDATES ACCOUNTABLE, I
ALSO RECOGNIZE WHY A LOT OF
YOUNG PEOPLE QUESTION WHETHER
THEIR VOTES MATTER, I BELIEVE
THAT THAT'S ONE REASON WHY WE
NEED VERY STRAIGHTFORWARD
REFORMS LIKE AN ELECTORAL
COLLEGE REFORM THAT WOULD SWITCH
IT TO JUST ELECTING OUR
PRESIDENT BASED ON THE PERSON
WHO GETS THE MOST VOTES TO ■W■W
SOMETHING ABOUT MONEY AND
POLITICS AND REDISTRICTING AND
ALL THESE THINGS WE'VE TALKED
ABOUT FOR YEARS, THEY'VE ALWAYS
BEEN IMPORTANT BUT NEVER SEEN AS
URGENT.
I THINK THAT CRITIQUE OF YOUNG
PEOPLE OF THINKING TWICE BEFORE
WE GET INVOLVED IN POLITICS, IN
THE SHORT TERM, I HOPE TO DEFEAT
THAT BY GETTING MORE YOUNG
PEOPLE INVOLVED IN POLITICS.
BUT IN THE LONG TERM I HOPE TO
MAKE OUR POLITICS MORE INCLUSIVE
SO THE YOUNG PEOPLE NEVER HAVE
TO ASK THAT QUESTION, DOES MY
VOICE MATTER?
>> MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIEG, THANK
YOU.
THANK YOU TO OUR AUDIENCE
TONIGHT WHO HAVE BEEN WITH US
FOR THE LAST FIVE HOURS.
INCREDIBLE NIGHT.
WE'VE NEVER DONE ANYTHING LIKE
THAT.
THANK YOU ALL.
WE WANT TO THANK THE INSTITUTE
OF POLITICS.
UP NEXT, MY COLLEAGUE IS PICKING
UP OUR COVERAGE OF THE SPECIAL
TO HALL EVENT LIVE FROM NEW
YORK, WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
■■■■
♪♪
Applebee's Bigger, Bolder
Grill Combos.
Now that's Eatin Good
in the Neighborhood.
I like to make my life easy.
■X
( ♪♪ )
Romo mode.
(Beep)
(Bang)
Good luck
with that one.
Yes!
That's why I wear
Skechers Slip-Ons.
They're effo.
Just slip them
right on and off.
Skechers
Slip-Ons,
with
Air-Cooled
Memory Foam.