SO, YOU KNOW, DO THEY DO A
SERIES OF HEARINGS OR DO THEY GO
IMMEDIATELY TO IT?
I THINK MOST DEMOCRATS WHO ARE
IN LEADERSHIP, WHO ARE LEADING
COMMITTEES WANT TO DO HEARINGS
FIRST.
IN PART BECAUSE THEY THINK THE
PUBLIC CASE NEEDS TO BE BUILT.
A LOT OF THE STUFF IN THE
MUELLER REPORT WASN'T TOTALLY
SHOCKING, AS IT'S BEEN REPORTED.
AND THEY NEED TO HAVE PEOPLE
TESTIFY, HAVE DRAMATIC MOMENTS,
SO THAT THE PUBLIC IS BEHIND
THEM A LITTLE BIT.
OR THEY CAN SEE THAT.
AND I THINK THAT'S PART OF THE
CALCULATION THAT THEY'RE MAKING
>> BILL, ONE OF THE OTHER FEARS,
AS YOU HEARD CONGRESSWOMAN
HOLMES NORTON SAY IS THAT THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE, IF THERE ARE
ALL OF THESE HEARINGS, IN WHICH
ALL OF THESE HORRIBLE STORIES
ABOUT DONALD TRUMP COME OUT,
THERE AREN'T THE SAME HEARINGS
AND ATTENTION, AT LEAST, ON
HEALTH CARE, JOBS, THINGS THAT
VOTERS OUT THERE CARE ABOUT MORE
THAN THEY DO ABOUT IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDINGS.
>> I THINK THE DEMOCRATS ARE
OVERTHINKING THIS.
THE DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATE WILL LAY OUT A PROGRAM
ON HEALTH CARE, JOBS, AND ALL OF
THAT.
IT'S PROBABLY NOT GOING TO MAKE
IT THROUGH THE SENATE OR GET
SIGNED BY THE PRESIDENT.
SO, FINE, THEY CAN HAVE A
HEARING HERE AND GO TO THE FLOOR
OF THE HEALTH CARE BILL THERE.
I DON'T THINK THIS IS ASKING TOO
MUCH OF THEM.
AND I THINK THE DYNAMIC NOW IS
GOING TO SET IN.
IF YOU TAKE THE REPORT
SERIOUSLY, IT'S VERY HARD TO SAY
THERE SHOULDN'T AT LEAST BE
HEARINGS TO SAY WHAT HAPPENED,
WITH FACT WITNESSES LIKE DON
McGAHN.
ONCE THREE HEARINGS HAPPEN, YOU
CAN DO THEM FASTER OR SLOWER.
AT SOME POINT, UYOU'LL HAVE TO
SAY, WE'VE HAD THE HEARINGS,
WHAT DO WE DO.
MAYBE YOU AGREE YOU CAN CENSURE
THE PRESIDENT IF YOU CAN GET
SOME REPUBLICANS ONBOARD.
BUT THE IDEA THIS IS GOING TO
FIZZLE OUT, I DON'T BUY THAT.
AND I DON'T THINK THE DEMOCRATS
WILL PAY A PRICE FOR GOING IN AN
ORDERLY, VERY LEGALISTIC WAY,
TOWARDS IMPEACHMENT, PERHAPS
VOTING FOR IMPEACHMENT, IT WILL
FAIL IN THE SENATE AND WE'LL
HAVE A PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN.
I DON'T THINK THIS DAMAGES THE
DEMOCRATS IN ANY IMPORTANT WAY.
>> I ALSO WANT TO TALK ABOUT
STEPHEN MOORE, THE PRESIDENT'S
PICK TO SERVE ON THE FEDERAL
RESERVE BOARD.
SABRINA'S K-FILE FOUND A COLUMN
THAT HE WROTE IN WHICH HE
ASSAILED THE IDEA OF WOMEN
PARTICIPATING AS REFEREES IN
PROFESSIONAL SPORTS.
HE ATTACKED FEMALE ATHLETES
PUSHING FOR EQUAL PAY, SAYING
THEY WANTED EQUAL PAY FOR
INFERIOR WORK.
HE MOCKED A READER WHO CALLED
HIS COLUMN SEXIST.
IN 2002, STEPHEN MOORE WROTE,
HERE'S THE RULE CHANGE I
PROPOSE, NO WOMEN ANYTHING,
THERE IS, OF COURSE, AN
EXCEPTION TO THIS RULE, WOMEN
ARE PERMITTED TO PARTICIPATE IF
AND ONLY THEY LOOK LIKE BONNIE
BERNSTEIN.
THE FACT THAT BONNIE KNOWS
NOTHING ABOUT BASKETBALL IS
ENTIRELY IRRELEVANT, UNQUOTE.
HE LATER WROTE THAT BERNSTEIN,
WHO WAS A CBS SPORTS JOURNALIST
AT THE TIME SHOULD WEAR HALTER
STOPS.
MOORE SAID THIS IS A SPOOF, HE'S
JUST JOKING, HE HAS A SENSE OF
HUMOR.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF IT?
>> I THINK PEOPLE ARE STRUGGLING
TO FIND OUT WHAT THE JOKE IS IN
THE COLUMNS THAT HE WROTE.
IT'S NOT SOME FLIPPANT COMMENT
HE MADE.
HE WENT OUT OF HIS WAY TO
EXPRESS THESE VIEWS, WHETHER HE
THOUGHT THEY WERE FUNNY OR NOT,
AND TO DO SO IN NOT JUST ONE
ISOLATED CASE, BUT IN MULTIPLE
WRITINGS.
AND I THINK THIS IS REFLECTIVE
OF A BROADER ATTITUDE TOWARDS
WOMEN THAT EMANATES FROM THE TOP
LEVEL OF THE WHITE HOUSE.
THE PRESIDENT HIMSELF HAS MADE A
LOT OF DEROGATORY COMMENTS WHEN
IT COMES TO WOMEN.
AND SO FOR MANY PEOPLE, THEY
MAG
MIGHT SAY THERE WAS A PROBLEM
HERE IN THIS VETTING THIS
CANDIDATE.
BUT QUITE FRANKLY, THIS WHITE
HOUSE HAS SHOWN TIME AND AGAIN
WHEN THEY HAVE THESE NOMINEES
THAT HAVE COME UNDER
CONTROVERSY, THE ADMINISTRATION
HAS STOOD BY THEM.
AND THAT'S BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT
HIMSELF BELIEVES THAT THESE ARE
THE PEOPLE HE WANTS FOR THE JOB.
AND THERE ARE OTHER CHALLENGES
WITH STEPHEN MOORE AND
REPUBLICANS HAVE RAISED CONCERNS
OVER THE FACT THAT HE IS A
POLITICAL OPERATIVE AND SO THAT
IS AT ODDS WITH WHAT YOU
TRADITIONALLY SEE FOR NOMINEES,
TRADITIONALLY INDEPENDENT
FEDERAL RESERVE.
AND I FIND IT CHALLENGING TO
THINK THAT THERE WOULD BE ENOUGH
SUPPORT FOR HIM IN A
REPUBLICAN-LED SENATE.
>> AND THE PRESIDENT ANNOUNCED
TODAY THAT HERMAN CAIN, WHO WAS
ALSO UP FOR A POSITION ON THE
FEDERAL RESERVE, HAS TAKEN
HIMSELF OUT OF THE RUNNING.
REPUBLICAN SENATOR TOLD ME,
HERMAN CAIN JUST DIDN'T HAVE THE
VOTES.
>> HERMAN CAIN WAS NEVER GOING
TO MAKE IT THAT FAR.
REPUBLICANS ON CAPITOL HILL KNEW
THAT AND THEY WERE MAKING IT
PRETTY CLEAR TO THE WHITE HOUSE.
PEOPLE INSIDE THE WHITE HOUSE
GOT THAT MESSAGE.
SO THEY THOUGHT BETWEEN THE TWO
OF THESE, STEPHEN MOORE WAS MORE
LIKELY TO ADVANCE, TO ACTUALLY
HAVE AN ATTEMPT TO GET ON IT AND
GO UNDER CONFIRMATION.
THEY DID NOT THINK THAT HERMAN
CAIN WAS GOING TO MAKE IT
ANYWAYS.
>> IN ADDITION TO THE QUESTIONS
ABOUT HIS QUALIFICATIONS,
QUESTIONS ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT
HE HAD SEXUALLY HARASSED WOMEN
IN HIS PREVIOUS POSITION, HE
DENIES THAT.
EVERYONE, STICK AROUND.
NEW DETAILS ON THE AMERICANS
KILLED IN ONE OF THE DEADLIEST
TERRORIST ATTACKS SINCE 9/11.
AND REPORTS OF IGNORED WARNING
SIGNS BY THE GOVERNMENT OF SRI
LANKA.
COULD THE EASTER SUNDAY ATTACKS
ON CHRISTIAN HAVE SAID STOPPED?
STAY WITH US.
Who's idea was this?
♪
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
♪
from any one else.
So why accept it
from your allergy pills?
Most pills don't finish the job
because they don't
relieve nasal congestion.
Flonase Allergy Relief
is different.
Flonase relieves sneezing,
itchy, watery eyes
and a runny nose, plus nasal
congestion, which pills don't.
Flonase helps block
6 key inflammatory substances.
Most pills only block one.
And 6 is greater than 1.
Start your day
with Flonase
for more complete
allergy relief.
Flonase.
This changes everything.
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
- [Woman] With my Shark,
I deep clean messes like this.
This and even this.
But I don't have to clean this,
because the self-cleaning
brush roll removes hair,
while I clean.
- [Announcer] Shark,
the vacuum that deep
cleans, now cleans itself.
(Burke)
At Farmers, we've seen almost
everything,
so we know how to
cover almost anything.
Even Rooftop Parking.
Strange forces at work?
Only if you're referring to
gravity-and we covered it.
Talk to Farmers.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
Carl, I appreciate
the invite here.
As my broker,
what am I paying you
to manage my money?
It's racquetball time.
(Thumps)
Ugh!
Carl, does your firm offer
a Satisfaction Guarantee?
Like Schwab does.
Guarantee?
(Splash)
Carl, can you remind me
what you've invested
my money in?
It's complicated.
Are you asking enough questions
about the way your wealth
is being managed?
If not, talk to Schwab.
A modern approach to Wealth
Management.
We call it the Mother
Standard of Care.
It's the idea that if
our mothers
were diagnosed
with cancer,
how would we want
them to be treated?
That's exactly how
we care for you.
With answers and actions.
To hear your concerns,
quiet your fears,
lift your spirits.
That's the Mother
Standard of Care.
This is how we
inspire hope.
This is how we heal.
Cancer Treatment
Centers of America.
Appointments available now.
Six months, six pushups ready.
Up.
Down.
Ah ah!
That's one.
Up.
That's two.
Down.
Get down,
get down.
>>> OUR WORLD LEAD NOW.
CNN LEARNING THIS AFTERNOON THAT
A FIFTH GRADE BOY FROM
WASHINGTON, D.C., IS ONE OF THE
ALMOST 300 FATALITIES AND ONE OF
THE DEADLIEST TERRORIST ATTACKS
SINCE 9/11.
U.S. INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS TELL
CNN THAT THE SERIES OF
COORDINATED EXPLOSIONS THAT
ROCKED SRI LANKA ON EASTER
SUNDAY WERE LIKELY INSPIRED BY
ISIS.
AT LEAST FOUR AMERICANS ARE
CURRENTLY AMONG THE 300 DEAD.
CNN'S SAM KILEY REPORTS THIS ALL
COMES AS THE SRI LANKAN
GOVERNMENT IS NOW APOLOGIZI
FOR FAILING TO HEED INTELLIGENCE
M BOTH THE U.S. AND ■@■@■@ Repo
SHOWS ONE OF THE ALLEGED SUICIDE
BOMBERS CARRYING WHAT CHURCH
OFFICIALS BELIEVE IS A BOMB IN
HIS BACKPACK.
HE PATS A TODDLER ON THE HEAD AS
HE CROSSES THE CHURCH COURTYARD.
SRI LANKAN TV IDENTIFYING HIM AS
A SUSPECT IN ONE OF THE ?8?8?8?
THE NE PRIESTS SAY, b■■T■í■í■LO■
SHOWS HÑ■■■Ñ■■■Ñ■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
KILLING AT LEAST 122 PEOPLE WHO
WERE CELEBRATING EASTER MASS.
>> IT BLASTED IN SUCH A WAY
THERE WERE CHILDREN AND WOMEN,
ALL CLOSE BY, AND ALL WERE BLOWN
UP ALMOST.
SO WE HAD HUNDREDS, MORE THAN 1
HURRICANE PEOPLE WHO WERE KILLED
ON THE SPOT.
THE SRI LANKAN MILITARY SAYS AT
LEAST SIX SUICIDE BOMBERS HAVE
THOUGHT TO HAVE ATTACKED TWO
OTHER CHURCHES AND THREE
FIVE-STAR HOTELS WITHIN MINUTES
OF ONE ANOTHER.
ALL AROUND THE TIME.
LOCAL AND U.S. INTELLIGENCE
OFFICIALS BELIEVE THAT THIS
SLICKLY COORDINATED PLOT IS THE
WORK OF AN INTERNATIONAL
ISIS-INSPIRED TERROR GROUP.F F
AN IT COULD STRIKE AGAIN SOON.
ACROSS THE ENTIRE COUNTRY, WITH
A STATE OF EMERGENCY ANNOUNCED,
AS THEY UNCOVERED MORE OF THE
MURDEROUS PLOT.
IN  A BOMB SQUAD
PERFORMED A CONTROLLED EXPLOSION
OF A SUSPICIOUS VAN NEAR ST.
ANTHONY'S CHURCH, ONE OF THE
SCENES OF SUNDAY'S ATTACK.
AND A 6-FOOT PIPE BOMB WAS FOUND
CLOSE TO THE AIRPORT, ALO■@ W■
NEARLY 90 BOMB DETONATORS AT THE
CITY'S BUS STOP.
SRI LANKA'S GOVERNMENT HAD
WARNINGS FROM U.S. AND INDIA
THAT ATTACKS WERE IMMINENT AND
PUBLICLY APOLOGIZED FOR FAILING
TO HEED THEM.
>> VERY, VERY SORRY.
>> Reporter: ON APRIL THE 11th,
A MEMO FROM THE DEPUTY INSPECTOR
GENERAL OF POLICE ADVISED■■ SRI
LANKAN OFFICIALS TO RAISE■
SECURITY DUE TO A POTENTIAL
ATTACK.
THE GOVERNMENT SPOKESMAN CAN'T
HIDE THE TRUTH FROM THE FAMILIES
OF MORE THAN 500 INJURED AND
NEARLY 300 DEAD, FOUR OF THEM
AMERICANS.
>> AS THE GOVERNMENT, WE HAVE TO
SAY AND WE HAVE TO APOLOGIZE TO
THE FAMILIES AND THE
INSTITUTIONS ABOUT THIS
INCIDENT.
>> Reporter: NOW THE CLEANUP
BEGINS.
>> ALL THE PEOPLE ARE SHOUTING,
WEEPING, AND W REALIZE  BUILD U
WE CAN'T BUILD UP OUR LIVES.
>> NOW, JAKE, AMONG THE DEAD,
FIFTH GRADER, KIRAN DESOSA, A
YOUNG LAD FROM WASHINGTON, D.C.,
AND DIETER KOWALSKI, A YOUNG MAN
FROM DENVER, COLORADO.
BOTH OF THEM KILLED IN■■■■■■■■■S
A■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
STATE OF EMERGENCY NOW COMING
INTO FO■■■S COULD GET
POTENTIALLY WORSE.
JAKE?
>> SAM KILEY IN SRI LANKA, THANK
YOU SO MUCH FOR THAT REPORT.
JOINING ME NOW IS FORMER CIA
COUNTERTERRORISM ANALYST, PHIL
MUDD, AND FORMER FBI SUPERVISORY
SPECIAL AGENT, JOSH CAMPBELL.
EXCUSE ME, JOSH, EXCUSE ME.
BOTTOM LINE, WAS THIS AN
INTELLIGENCE FAILURE?
I THINK IT'S TOO SOON TO SAY
THAT, JAKE.
WHEN I WAS IN THE FBI, I SERVED
ON ONE OF OUR GLOBAL TEAMS
RESPONSIBLE FOR CONDUCTING
INVESTIGATIONS IN SOUTHEAST ASIA
AND WE ROUTINELY SHARED
INFORMATION WITH OUR
COUNTERPARTS.
WE DON'T KNOW YET IF THIS IS
INFORMATION THAT CAME FROM
WESTERN OFFICIALS, BUT IF THAT'S
THE CASE, I'VE SEEN THESE TYPES
OF REPORTS THAT HAVE BEEN HANDED
OVER SOMETIMES.
THEY'RE VERY RICH IN DETAIL,
SOMETIMES THEY'RE VERY VAGUE.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT INFORMATION
WAS PASSED ON YET.
ONCE WE GET A GREATER SENSE OF
WHAT THAT IS, THEN WE'LL BE IN A
BETTER POSITION TO DECIDE
WHETHER THIS IS A FAILURE.
>> I APOLOGIZE FOR THE SNEEZE.
IT IS POLLEN SEASON HERE IN
WASHINGTON, D.C.
PHIL, I WANT TO ASK ABOUT WHAT
JOSH JUST SAID.
BECAUSE SOMETIMES YOU HEAR,
THERE'S A WARNING AND THE
GOVERNMENT DIDN'T HEAR IT.
FROM WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT THE
WARNING THAT THE UNITED STATES
PROVIDED, THAT INDIA PROVIDED,
IS THAT ENOUGH THAT COULD HAVE
PREVENTED THIS HORRIFIC ATTACK?
I MEAN, AS FAR AS I KNOW, IT
DIDN'T SAY, THESE ATTACKE
GOIN TARGETING CHRISTIANS
WORSHIPING ON EASTER.
>> IF YOU WANT TO STUDY A
WARNING, I WOULD JUST ASK YOU TO
LOOK FOR A FEW SPECIFICS.
YOU HAVE TIME, PLACE, PEOPLE,
DEVICE.
THOSE FOUR CHARACTERISTICS.
IF YOU HAVE A GENERAL WARNING
SOMETHING MIGHT BE COMING UP IN
A COUNTRY OF 22 MILLION, 23
MILLION PEOPLE, IN MY
INTELLIGENCE WORLD, YOU HAVE TO
HAVE SPECIFICITY TO GO TO
OFFICIALS AND SAY, HERE'S THE
PLACE YOU WANT TO GUARD, HERE'S
THE KIND OF DEVICE YOU MIGHT
WANT TO LOOK AT, HERE'S WHAT THE
CELL LOOKS LIKE.
A GENERIC WARNING MIGHT SOUND
UGLY TO THE GENERAL PUBLIC.
IN MY WORLD, THAT'S A DIME A
DOZEN.
YOU NEED MORE THAN THAT.
>> AND THE LEVEL OF COORDINATION
HERE WAS EXTRAORDINARY.
THREE DIFFERENT CITIES, EIGHT
DIFFERENT EXPLOSIONS, CHURCHES
WERE TARGETED, WESTERN HOTELS
WERE TARGETED.
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU ABOUT
WHO CONDUCTED THIS?
>> YEAH, NO QUESTION THIS WAS
HIGHLY SOPHISTICATED.
AND WE'VE HEARD REPORTS THAT
THIS MAY HAVE BEEN ISIS
INSPIRED.
I TEND TO SUSPECT THAT'S
PROBABLY THE CASE HERE BASED ON
A NUMBER OF CHARACTERISTICS.
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
DIRECTED AND INSPIRED.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN AN ACTUAL CLAIM
OF RESPONSIBILITY COMING OUT
FROM ISIS.
BUT THIS IS THE ONE THING THAT
WE'VE ALL WORRIED ABOUT, PEOPLE
GOING TO THE BATTLEFIELD AND
WHERE DO DAY GO NEXT?
WHERE DO THEY TAKE THAT HATRED?
AND THIS IS EARLY ON, BUT IT
APPEARS THIS TYPE OF INSPIRATION
WAS AT LEAST AT PLAY HERE.
>> PHIL, TAKE A LISTEN TO THE
SECRETARY OF STATE MIKE POMPEO
SPEAKING TODAY ON THE THREAT
FROM ISIS AND OTHER TERRORIST
GROUPS.
>> THE DESTRUCTION OF THE
CALIPHATE WAS IMPORTANT AND IT
MATTERED.
AND THE TAKEDOWN OF THESE
THREATS FROM OTHER GEOGRAPHIES
AS WELL.
BUT, SADLY, THIS EVIL EXISTS IN
THE WORLD.
>> "WE HAVE TAKEN DOWN THE
THREAT SUBSTANTIALLY, BUT
OBVIOUSLY, THE EVIL DOES EXIST
IN THE WORLD."
IS THERE -- I MEAN, ASSUMING
THIS GROUP WAS ISIS INSPIRED,WH
INTELLIGENCE THINKS NOW, I MEAN,
DOES THAT -- IS THERE ANYTHING
THAT CHANGED VIS-A-VIS SYRIA AND
IRAQ AND THE DEFEAT OF ISIS AND
THE CALIPHATE, THE GEOGRAPHICAL
CALIPHATE THERE VERSUS SRI
LANKA.
DOES IT HAVE ANY EFFECT?
>> YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE, DESPITE
THIS EVENT TODAY, THAT THE
THREAT DIMINISHES OVER TIME.
FOR EXAMPLE, IN EUROPE COMPARED
TO WHERE WE WERE THREE, FOUR
YEARS AGO, YOU CAN'T GET TO
SYRIA TO TRAIN.
SO BY DEFINITION, YOU'LL HAVE
FEWER PEOPLE COMING BACK WITH
HIGH TECH SKILLS.
THAT SAID, THIS IDEA THAT A
GEOGRAPHICAL FATE AND THE
DECLINE OF A GEOGRAPHICAL FATE
IS THE END GAME, ISIS AND KAL
QAEDA WERE IDEAS THAT CAN BE
DISSEMINATED ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
THAT'S SEEN RIGHT NOW IN SRI
LANKA, SO LET'S NOT FOCUS TOO
MUCH ON STATEMENTS ABOUT THE
DECLINE OF CALIPHATE.
I WANT TO SEE THE DECLINE OF THE
IDEA.
>> PHIL MUDD AND JOSH CAMPBELL,
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE ARE JUST HOURS AWAY FROM ONE
OF THE BUSIEST NIGHTS AND THE
BIGGEST NIGHTS OF THE 2020
CAMPAIGN SO FAR, AS THE
DEMOCRATIC FIELD KEEPS GROWING.
STAY WITH US.
en it comes to rede
sugar in your family's diet,
Coke, Dr Pepper and Pepsi hear
you.
We're working together to do
just that.
Bringing you more great tasting
beverages with less sugar
or no sugar at all.
Smaller portion sizes,
clear calorie labels and
reminders to think balance.
Because we know mom wants what's
best.
More beverage choices, smaller
portions, less sugar.
BalanceUS.org
PNC Bank has technology to
help make banking easier,
like..
PNC Easy Lock,
so you can easily lock
your credit card
when its maximum limit differs
from its vertical limit.
and Clover Flex,
for when you need to
take credit cards
when no one carries cash.
or requesting a call to help
get a new credit card-
one that hasn't followed
the family goldfish.
PNC — Make today the day.
♪ ♪
Plants capture CO2.
What if other kinds of plants
captured it too?
If these industrial plants had
technology
that captured carbon like trees
we could help lower emissions.
Carbon Capture is important
technology -
and experts agree.
That's why we're working on ways
to improve it.
So plants...
can be a little more...
like plants.
♪ ♪
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
Hmm. Exactly.
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay for
what you need.
Nice. But, uh...
what's up with
your... partner?
Oh. Well, we just spend
all day telling everyone
how we customize
car insurance,
because no two people
are alike, so...
LiMu gets a
little confused
when he sees
another bird
that looks
exactly like him.
[ loud crash ]
Yeah.
He'll figure it out.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
>>> THE 2020 LEAD TODAY, A
SWELLING FIELD OF DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES WITH 19
NAMES NOW IN THE RACE AND MORE
ON THE WAY.
AND A YOUTUBE VIDEO RELEASED
THIS MORNING, MARINE CORPS
VETERAN TURNED CONGRESSMAN SETH
MOULTON OF MASSACHUSETTS
ANNOUNCED THAT HE, TOO, IS
RUNNING IN 2020.
BUT AS HE LAUNCHES HIS CAMPAIGN,
A DIFFERENT HIGH-PROFILE NAME
MAY QUICKLY STEAL THE SPOT.
AS CNN'S PHIL MATTINGLY REPORTS,
WE'RE LEARNING HOW FORMER VICE
PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN IS LIKELY
PLANNING HIS CAMPAIGN ROLLOUT
THIS WEEK.
>> Reporter: THE HISTORICALLY
■
OCR
>> BE HONORED IF YOU'D
JOIN ME IN THIS MISSION.
>> Reporter: -- NOW ADDING
ANOTHER CANDIDATE IN THE MIX.
>> I'M RUNNING BECAUSE I'M A
PATRIOT.
BECAUSE I BELIEVE IN THIS
COUNTRY, AND BECAUSE I'VE NEVER
WANTED TO SIT ON THE SIDELINES
WHEN IT COMES TO SERVING IT.
>> Reporter: SETH MOULTON
LAUNCHING HIS CAMPAIGN MONDAY.
BUT MOULTON'S ENTRANCE WON'T BE
THEP■ , WITH THE
■■ OWN
CAMPAIGN.
SOURCES TELL CNN VICE PRESIDENT
JOE BIDEN WHO LEADS THE FEEL IN
NATIONAL AND EARLY PRIMARY
CAUCUS STATE POLLING WILL PUT AN
END TO THE LONG-RUN WILLING HE
OR WON'T HE?
BIDEN IS EXPECTED TO ANNOUNCE
HIS CANDIDACY IN A VIDEOBS
WEEK, FOLLOWED BY TRAVEL TO
EARLY PRIMARY STATES NEXT WEEK.
BIDEN WOULD MAKE IT AN
ASTOUNDING 20 CANDIDATES
OFFICIALLY RUNNING TO TAKE ON
PRESIDENT TRUMP IN 2020, WITH
DISPARATE RECORDS, MESSAGES, AND
POTENTIAL COALITIONS, A FACT
THAT UNDERSCORES THE EFFORTS BY
ELIZABETH WARREN TO BREAK OUT ON
POLICY.
WARREN ON MONDAY RELEASING THE
MOST SWEEPING, AGGRESSIVE PLAN
TO CURTAIL THE ESTIMATED $1.5
TRILLION IN STUDENT LOAN DEAD, A
$1.25 TRILLION PLAN TO CANCEL
LOAN DEBT UP TO $50,000 FOR
HOUSEHOLDS EARNING LESS THAN
$100,000, IMPLEMENT FREE PUBLIC
COLLEGE, AND EXPAND GRANTS FOR
LOWER INCOME AND MINORITY
STUDENTS FOR HOUSING, FOOD, AND
BOOKS.
>> IT'S NOT JUST PAYING THE
TUITION.
IT'S HOW THEY PAY FOR BOOKS.
IT'S HOW THEY PAY FOR THE
EXPENSES OF HAVING A BABY TAKEN
CARE OF IF THEY ALREADY HAVE A
CHILD AT HOME OR BEING ABLE TO
COVER COMMUTING EXPENSES.
OR MAYBE IT'S A CHANCE TO LIVE
IN A DORM AND HAVE THE KIND OF
COLLEGE EXPERIENCE THAT OTHER
KIDS GET.
>> Reporter: WARREN TO PITCH
THAT PLANND MORE TONIGHT ON
CNN, WHEN SHE AND FOUR OTHER
CANDIDATES TAKE PART IN SERIES
OF TOWN HALLS FROM NEW
HAMPSHIRE, A PRIME-TIME EVENT
FOR FIVE TOP-TIER CANDIDATES,
ALL LOOKING TO BREAK OUT OF AN
INCREASINGLY EXPANDING PACK.
>> AND JAKE, SENATOR WARREN'S
ADVISERS MADE CLEAR THAT SHE
WILL MAKE CRYSTAL CLEAR TONIGHT
IN THE TOWN HALL THAT HER LANE,
THE ONE OF IN THE WEEDS POLICY
PROPOSALS, IS BOAST DURABLE AND
SOMETHING THAT WILL EVENTUALLY
LEAD HER BACK INTO THE TOP TIER
OF CANDIDATES.
IT'S A GAMBLE, ONE THEY
ACKNOWLEDGE, BUT ONE THEY
BELIEVE, EVEN THOUGH THERE'S
LAGGING FUND-RAISING AND LAGGING
POLL NUMBERS, THAT WILL
EVENTUALLY PAY OFF.
>> PHIL MATTINGLY IN NEW  THANK
PHIL.
AND SPEAKING OF NEW HAMPSHIRE,
WE'RE LEARNING THAT BIDEN IS
PLANNING TO VISIT IOWA THIS
WEEK, BUT HE TRAILS IN Añ■■■■■ç
5%, 4%.
SO I HAVE TO SAY, THAT IS A
STRONGER SHOWING THAN I WOULD
HAVE THOUGHT FOR BUTTIGIEG AND
A -- I MEAN, SECOND PLACE, IT'S
NOT BAD, BUT A WEAKER SHOWING
THAN I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT FOR
BIDEN, WHO HAS OBVIOUSLY BEEN
CAMPAIGNING FOR PRESIDENT OFF
AND ON SINCE 1987.
>> RIGHT, I THINK IT'S STILL
VERY MUCH A WIDE OPEN FIELD AND
IT'S VERY DIFFICULT TO MAKE
DETERMINATIONS BASED ON THE
EARLY POLLING, ESPECIALLY BEFORE
ANY OF THESE CANDIDATES APPEAR
ON THE DEBATE STAGE.
NOW, IT'S NOT UNUSUAL FOR BERNIE
SANDERS OR JOE BIDEN, THE PEOPLE
WHO HAVE THE MOST NAME
RECOGNITION TO BE AT THE TOP OF
THE PACK.
IT HAS CERTAINLY BEEN IMPRESSIVE
TO MANY PEOPLE THAT MAYOR PETE
BUTTIGIEG, WHO IS RELATIVELY
UNKNOWN UNTIL JUST A COUPLE OF
MONTHS AGO, AS SORT OF SHOT TO
THIS TOP TIER OF CANDIDATES IN
THE EYES OF MANY.
I THINK A LOT OF THE QUESTIONS
THAT WILL BE RESOLVED IN THE
EYES OF VOTERS WILL BE TWOFOLD.
THERE WILL BE THE POLICY
DISAGREEMENTS AND WHAT
VARIATIONS ON HEALTH CARE OR A
FREE COLLEGE TUITION OR
EDUCATION, YOU KNOW, THE POLICY
PROPOSALS THAT THEY WILL PUT
OUT.
AND THEN, OF COURSE, THERE'S THE
ELEPHANT IN THE ROOM, WHICH IS,
WHAT WILL BE THEIR APPROACH TO
TAKING ON DONALD TRUMP AND WHAT
ARE SOME OF THE QUESTIONS AROUND
IMPEACHMENT AND THE POST-MUELLER
DEBATE THAT THEY'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO CONTEND WITH AS
CANDIDATES.
>> SPEAKING OF COLLEGE LOAN
DEBT, BERNIE SANDERS IN 2016
CAMPAIGNED HEAVILY ON A PLAN OF
FREE TUITION.
ELIZABETH WARREN SAYS HER NEW
PLAN GOES FURTHER, BECAUSE IT
ADDS ON GETTING RID OF STUDENT
LOAN DEBT.
DO YOU BUY HER ARGUMENT THAT
EVENTUALLY ALL OF THESE POLICY
ROLLOUTS ARE GOING TO PAY OFF
FOR HER?
I HAVE TO SAY, 4%, SHE'S FROM
NEIGHBORING MASSACHUSETTS.
SHE ALSO IS A NATIONAL FIGURE
AND A KNOWN ENTITY.
THAT IS NOT AS STRONG A SHOWING
AS I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT AMONG
NEW HAMPSHIRE DEMOCRATS.
>> I THINK THAT'S RIGHT.
AND IF YOU'RE HER TEAM, I THINK
YOU'RE TRYING TO FIND WAYS TO
HAVE TRACTION AT THIS POINT.
OBVIOUSLY, SHE WINS THE POLICY
PRIMARY, BUT WINNING THE POLICY
PRIMARY DOESN'T TYPICALLY WIN
THE PRESIDENTIAL PRIMARY.
SHE CAME OUT STRONGLY FOR
IMPEACHMENT.
I THINK THAT WAS CLEARLY AN
EFFORT TO GAIN TRACTION AT TIME
WHEN SHE WAS NOT.
SHE ALSO HAS BEEN SPENDING
ALMOST AS SHE'S BEEN RAISING SO
IF YOU'RE ON HER INTERNAL TEAM,
YOU'RE LOOKING AT THE RACE RIGHT
NOW AND YOU'RE THINKING, WE HAVE
COUPLE OF MONTHS TO GAIN
TRACTION AND REALLY MAKE A MOVE
HERE.
SHE WAS BERNIE SANDERS ARGUABLY
BEFORE BERNIE SANDERS WAS BERNIE
SANDERS.
AND SHE PROBABLY SHOULD HAVE RUN
FOUR YEARS AGO.
AND SHE MAYBE COULD HAVE WON THE
PRIMARY, BUT THAT DOESN'T MATTER
AT THIS POINT.
I THINK AT THIS POINT, SHE HAS
TO DECIDE IF SHE CAN MAKE
TRACTION TO STILL BE IN THE RACE
IN THE FALL.
>> OF COURSE, THE INEVITABLE
QUESTION, WHO'S GOING TO PAY FOR
IT, WILL IT'S STUDENT LOAN DEAD
OR COLLEGE TUITION.
ELIZABETH WARREN PREEMPTIVELY
PUT OUT A PLAN TO TAX WHAT SHE
CALLS THE VERY RICH, AND SAYS
THAT WILL HELP WITH OTHER WAYS
TO TAX THE VERY RICH.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> FOR TWO CENTS ON THE DOLLAR,
WE COULD PAY FOR UNIVERSAL CHILD
CARE, UNIVERSAL PRE-K, UNIVERSAL
COLLEGE AND NOT BACK THE STUDENT
LOAN DEBT BURDEN FOR ABOUT 43
MILLION AMERICANS AND STILL HAVE
NEARLY JUST SHORT OF $1 TRILLION
LEFT OVER.
>> THAT, OF COURSE, WILL BE
PORTRAYED IF SHE BECOMES THE
NOMINEE BY DONALD TRUMP AS SHE
WANTS TO TAX YOU, SHE WANTS TO
TAX YOU, NOT JUST THE WEALTHY,
BUT ALL OF YOU.
>> IT DOESN'T SEEM TO BE THE
POLICY DIFFERENCES BETWEEN THE
DEMOCRATS ARE GOING TO BE
DISPOSITIVE.
THEY'RE ALL GOING TO BE FOR SOME
VERSIONS OF, OBVIOUSLY,
EXPANDING HEALTH CARE AND
HELPING WITH TUITION AND SO
FORTH.
I GUESS SANDERS STRIKES ME AS
THE ONE WHO'S DISTINCT.
I THINK THERE'S A CERTAIN NUMBER
OF -- IT WILL BE SANDERS AND
PROBABLY EVERYONE ELSE, I THINK.
AND SANDERS SEEMS TO BE THE ONE
CANDIDATE WHO'S GOT A REAL BASE.
HE SEEMS TO BE STICKING RIGHT AT
30% IN THE POLLS.
FOR ME THE LESSON IN THAT NEW
HAMPSHIRE POLL IS THAT THIS IS
WILL PROBABLY STAY AT 30, BUT
IT'S ALMOST AS LIKELY THAT
SOMEONE WE'VE NEVER HEARD OF,
BUTTIGIEG TWO MONTHS AGO, COULD
EASILY BE THE MAIN CHALLENGER.
NO JOE BIDEN, NOT ELIZABETH
WARREN OR KAMALA HARRIS.
OR IT COULD BE A THREE OR FOUR
OR FIVE-WAY RACE WITH SOME OF
THOSE OTHER CANDIDATES.
MAYBE SETH MOULTON WILL TAKE
OFF, AND WE'LL HAVE THE
MOULTON/AND BUTTIGIEG YOUNG
VETERANS IN THEIR 30s.
>> ADD TULSI GABBARD TO THAT.
AND AMY KLOBUCHAR WILL BE IN THE
TOWN HALL THIS EVENING, THE
SENATOR FROM MINNESOTA.
HER ARGUMENT IS THAT SHE CAN WIN
IN TRUMP COUNTRY.
SHE HAS BEEN A VERY POPULAR VOTE
GETTER IN MINNESOTA, WHICH
ALMOST WENT FOR TRUMP, BUT SHE'S
WON OVER TRUMP COUNTIES.
TAKE A LISTEN TO HER MAKING THIS
ARGUMENT.
>> I'M FROM THE MIDDLE OF THE
COUNTRY, I'M THE ONLY ONE IN THE
RACE THAT HAS REPEATEDLY WON
TRUMP COUNTIES AND TRUMP
DISTRICTS, TO THE POINT WHERE
THREE TIMES IN A ROW, I HAVE WON
EVERY SINGLE CONGRESSIONAL
DISTRICT IN MY STATE, INCLUDING
THE RURAL ONES.
>> AND FOR DEMOCRATS WHO WANT TO
WIN, THAT COULD BE A COMPELLING
ARGUMENT.
>> AND THAT'S WHAT SHE'S SAYING,
ESSENTIALLY, I COULD BEAT TRUMP.
THAT'S WHY SHE'S SAYING SHE
COULD WIN THOSE COUNTIES.
AND THAT'S WHAT THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN AND THE TRUMP WHITE
HOUSE SEEMS TO BE MORE CONCERNED
ABOUT.
IF THEY COULD RUN AGAINST A
BERNIE SANDERS, THAT IS
ESSENTIALLY THEIR DREAM.
THEY FEEL LIKE THAT'S A PRETTY
EASY CAMPAIGN FOR THEM TO SET
UP.
THEY CAN DRAW A STARK CONTRAST
BETWEEN THE PRESIDENT AND PEOPLE
LIKE ELIZABETH WARREN AND BERNIE
SANDERS, BUT NOT SO MUCH WITH
PEOPLE LIKE AMY KLOBUCHAR, WHO
HAS BEEN THE ONE CANDIDATE WHO
HAS NOT BEEN AFRAID TO SAY NO TO
SOME OF THOSE POLICY PROPOSALS,
LIKE MEDICARE FOR ALL AND THE
GREEN NEW DEAL.
SHE'S BEEN MUCH MORE MODERATE ON
THOSE PROPOSALS.
IS IT SOMEONE LIKE THAT THAT CAN
BEAT THE PRESIDENT?
IT DOESN'T SEEM OBVIOUSLY THAT
THEY KNOW EITHER WAY.
THEY DON'T KNOW IF THEY COULD GO
MORE EXTREME AND IMPEACH OR
FOLLOW THE AMY KLOBUCHAR ROUTE
AND THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN IS KIND
OF BANKING ON THEM NOT FIGURING
THAT OUT UNTIL THE END.
>> SETH MOULTON IS TALKING ABOUT
HOW HE DID FOUR TOURS IN IRAQ, A
MARINE VETERAN.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF HIS CHANCES?
HE'S NEW TODAY, SO I WANT TO
GIVE AN OPPORTUNITY TO CHEW OVER
HIM A LITTLE BIT.
IS HE OFFERING SOMETHING THAT
OTHER CANDIDATES ARE NOT?
>> I THINK HE'S JUST SOMEONE WHO
THINKS HE HAS NOTHING TO LOSE.
THERE ARE SOME CANDIDATES WHO
WANT TO EVALUATE THEIR PROFILE
AND HE'S SOMEONE WHO CHALLENGED
THE ESTABLISHMENT AND DEFEAT A
LONG-TERM INCUMBENT, IT SHOWS
THAT REALLY ANYONE CAN TRY TO
USE THIS OPPORTUNITY TO MAKE A
NAME FOR THEMSELVES.
>> AND YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS
TONIGHT'S CNN MAJOR TOWN HALL
EVENT LIFE IN MANCHESTER, NEW
HAMPSHIRE.
SENATOR AMY KLOBUCHAR UP AT 7:00
A.M. EASTERN, ELIZABETH WARREN
AT 8:00, BERNIE SANDERS AT 9:00,
KAMALA HARRIS A AT 10:00 AND
PETE BUTTIGIEG AT 11:00 P.M.
EASTERN.
>>> IN OUR EARTH MATTERS DAY,
CLIMATE CHANGE IS HAVING AN
EFFECT RIGHT NOW.
BUT AS CNN'S BILL WEIR
DISCOVERED, EVEN MANY OF THE
THOSE AMERICANS BEING HURT RIGHT
NOW DON'T BELIEVE THAT CLIMATE
CHANGE IS REAL. Reporter: IN TH
HEARTLAND, THEATá#e■F
2019 SETTING THE WORST KIND
CORDS.
IT WAS A MONTH AGO WHEN HEAVY
SNOW MELTED SO FAST AND A BOMB
CYCLONE RAINED SO HARD, WATER
OVERWHELMED THE ARMY CORPS OF
ENGINEERS AND LEVEES IN SIX
STATES.
THE FLOODWATERS CAME WITH SUCH
FORCE, THEY RIPPED OPEN GRAIN
SILOS ACROSS THE MIDWEST,
CONTAMINATING THE CROP WITH
TOXIC WATER AND RUINING
LIVELIHOOD OF SO MANY FARMERS
WHO HAD BEEN STORING THEIR GRAIN
IN ORDER TO SURVIVE THE TRADE
WAR WITH CHINA.
MOST AMERICAN PHAFARMS ARE NOT
FULLY INSURED AGAINST THIS KIND
OF DISASTER.
AND IN HAMBURG, IOWA, 70% OF THE
HOMES HAD NOLOOD INSURANCE AT
ALL.
MOLD IS SPREADING.
THE BALL FIELD IS STILL A LAKE.
AND DOWNTOWN IS A GHOST TOWN.E
THIS DAY IS A VISITOR FROM THE
WEST, HERE TO WARN THE NATION
THAT THIS IS JUSTa  BEGI
>> WE KNOW, UNFORTUNATELY, THAT
WHAT WE SEE HERE TODAY IS JUST A
PRECURSOR OF MANY, MANY MORE
INTENSE FLOODS IN THE FUTURE,
BECAUSE OF CLIMATE CHANGE.
>> PLEASE WELCOME GOVERNOR JAY
INSLEE.
>> Reporter: THE WASHINGTON
GOVERNOR IS THE FIRST PERSON IN
HISTORY TO BUILD A PRESIDENTIAL
CAMPAIGN AROUND CLIMATE CHANGE,
A TOPIC DISCUSSED FOR ABOUT FIVE
MINUTES IN THE LAST THREE
PRESIDENTIAL DEBATES.
>> YOU NEED, WHAT IS IT, 65,000
INDIVIDUAL DONORS TO GET ON A
STAGE AT THE DEBATE.
>> YOU PET.
>> HOW MANY YOU GOT NOW?
>> WE HAVE A WAYS TO GO.
>> IF YOU KEEP THIS TOPIC IN THE
DEBATE, IN THE MINDS OF VOTERS,
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE POLLING LESS
THAN 1%, IS THAT A VICTORY?
OR FOR YOU, ARE YOU REALLY
THINKING YOU HAVE A SHOT AT THE
OVAL OFFICE?
>> INTENT IS TOg■
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
THAT IOWA DEMOCRATS NOW LIST
CLIMATE CHANGE NEXT TO HEALTH
CARE AS A TOP CONCERN.
AND AFTERASTERS LIKE THIS,
YOU WOULD THINK EVEN SKEPTICAL
REPUBLICANS MIGHT JOIN THEM.
>> SO DO YOU HAVE WATER SERVICE
HERE NOW?
>> NO.
WE HAVE NO WATER AND NO HEAT.
>> Reporter: BUT RON PERRY DOWN
AT THE RISKY BUSINESS AUTO SHOP
IS NOT BUYING WHAT THE GOVERNOR
IS SELLING.
THE GOVERNOR IS HERE BECAUSE HE
BELIEVES THAT ALL OF THIS DAMAGE
THE DIRECT RESULT OF CLIMATE
CHANGE.
DO YOU SEE IT THAT WAY?
>> NO!
ABSOLUTELY NOT!
I BLAME IT ON THE CORPS OF
ENGINEERS, TOTALLY.
>> YOU CAN'T EXPECT THE ARMY
CORPS TO SOLVE THIS PROBLEM IF
THE TRUMP -- WHEN THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES IS TELLING
HIM TO IGNORE CLEAR SCIENCE.
>> HOW DO YOU CONVINCE A GUY
LIKE RON TO VOTE FOR YOU?
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW FOR SURE,
NOT EVERY -- I DON'T EXPECT
EVERYONE TO VOTE FOR ME.
JUST WELL OVER
>> NO, I GET THAT!
BUT, YOU USE THE MOONSHOT
ANALOGY.
WHEN KENNEDY SAID, WE'RE GOING
TO THE MOON, REPUBLICANS DIDN'T
ARGUE THAT THERE'S NO MOON.
AND THIS IS A MILLION MOONSHOTS
PUT TOGETHER.
>> WELL, I TELL YOU, THE WAY YOU
DO IT IS YOU DEFEAT DONALD
TRUMP.
DONALD TRUMP HAS BEEN TELLING
FOLKS THIS IS A CHINESE HOAX.
AND WHEN YOU HAVE SOMEONE THAT
IS SO WILLFULLY IGNORANT, THAT
PERSON HAS TO BE REMOVED FROM
PUBLIC LIFE.
AND THAT'S WHAT I INTEND TO DO.
LOOK, WHAT WINS SUPPORT HERE IS
A RECOGNITION OF ECONOMIC GROWTH
AND VITALITY.
THE FACT THAT WE'VE GOT JOBS AND
WIND TURBINES AND SOLAR POWER
AND ELECTRIC CARS AND BATTERIES.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HAVE AN
ARGUMENT ABOUT PARTS PER M
OF CARBON IF YOU'VE GOT A LOT OF
PEOPLE GOING TO.
AND THAT'S MY MEAGE.
>> Reporter: SINCE HIS STATE
JUST REJECTED A TAX ON CARBON,
THAT WOULD BE AN AMBITIOUS
FUTURE.
THIS IS THE GRIM PRESENT, A
DYING , PLANTING SEASON IN
PERIL, AND ANOTHER FLOOD WARNING
IN THE FORECAST.
BILL WEIR, CNN, HAMBURG, IOWA.
>> AND OUR THANKS, AS ALWAYS, TO
BILL WEIR FOR THAT REPORT.
ANY MOMENT NOW, SPEAKER NANCY
PELOSI IS GOING TO LEAD A
CONFERENCE CALL WITH HOUSE
DEMOCRATS TO DECIDE WLP
IMPEACHMENT IS THE RIGHT WAY
FORWARD FOR THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY.
STAY WITH US.
♪♪
AHHHH!
We're here.
♪♪
At Fidelity, we make sure you
have a clear plan
to cover the essentials
in retirement,
as well as all the things
you want to do.
Because when you're ready
for what comes next,
the only direction is forward.
♪♪
This is the family who booked
the flight,
who saved by adding a hotel,
which led to new adventures,
♪♪
that captured their
imaginations
♪♪
and turned moments into
memories.
With flights, hotels,
activities and more
for your Florida vacation,
Expedia has everything
you need to go.
1■ ■ ■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■8