FIRST TIME, WOLF, WE'RE SEEING
ON THE STAGE TIME BEFORE THE
SAME AUDIENCE THE ABILITY TO
COMPARE THESE CANDIDATES TO EACH
OTHER.
IT'S NOT A ONE OFF ????????? IS.
>> THIS IS MAJOR MOMENT.
FIVE KEY DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES ABOUT TO THIS■■■
STAGE.
PHIL AND DAVID, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
I'M WOLF BLITZER IN WASHINGTON.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
CNN'S PRESIDENTIAL TOWN HALLS
LIVE FROM MANCHEST, NEW
HAMPSHIRE, THEY START RIGHT NOWa
>>> GOOD EVE
WELCOME TO A CNN SPECIAL
DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL TOWN
HALL EVENT.
I'M CHRIS CUOMO.
WE ARE IN MANCHESTER, NUCHL.
THIS IS THE FIRST PRESIDENTIAL
PRIMARY SFAT.
NOW TONIGHT YOU'RE GOING TO HEAR
FROM FIVE OF THE TOP DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES ON THE
SAME STAGE FOR THE FIRST TIME.
YOU'VE GOT SENATORS AMY
KAMALA HARRIS ANDORE D■>
BUTTIGIEG.
EACH GETS O HOUR BUT TONIGHT
IS DIFFERENT FROM OTHER TOWN
HALLS.
THE POTENTIAL QUESTIONERS■■
ENTIRELY STUDENTS AND YOUNG
ADULTS REPRESENTING MORE THAN 30
STATES NATIONWIDE.
NOW TO PULL THIS OFF CNN HAS
PARTNERED WITH HARVARD
UNIVERSITY'S INSTITUTE OF
POLITICS WHICH JUST RELEASED ITS
YOUTH POLL EXAMINING THE
POLITICAL OPINIONS OF YOUNG
AMERICANS.
AND ALSO WE'RE WITH THE NEW
HAMPSHIRE INSTITUTE OF POLITICS
RIGHT HERE IN NEW HAMPSHIRE.
WHO HAS THE BEST PITCH FOR THAT
ALL IMPORTANT YOUNG VOTE?
TONIGHT YOU'RE GOING TO GET A
GREAT LOOK AT THAT.
FIRST OFF IN A RETURN TOWN HALL
HERE IS SENATOR AMY KLOBUCHAR OF
MINNESOTA, PITCHING HERSELF AS
THE CANDIDATE WHO CAN DEFEAT
PRESIDENT DONALD TRUMP IN THE
MIDWEST.
WELCOME, SENATOR.
PLEASE, COME ON OUT.
>> SENATOR, A PLEASURE.
PLEASE.
>> WOW, THANK YOU.
>> IT'S GOOD TO HAVE YOU.
LET'S GET RIGHT TO THE
QUESTIONS.
WE HAVE FALL OUT FROM THE
MUELORT AS A TOPIC.
OUR FIRST QUESTION IN OUR
AUDIENCE IS JOHN, FRESHMAN AT
HARVARD AT CAPETOWN,
MASSACHUSETTS.
>> SHOULD THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE MOVE FORWARD WITH
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS AGAINST
PRESIDENT TRUMP?
>> OKAY, SO I BELIEVE VERY
STRONGLY THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
SHOULD BE HELD ACCOUNTABLE.
WHEN YOU LOOK THROUGH THAT
REPORT IT IS APPALLING SOME OF
THE THINGS THAT WERE GOING ON.
AND YOU CAN SEE TIME AND TIME
AGAIN, MAYBE YOU'VE READ PARTS
OF IT, THAT WAS HIS ADVISERS
THAT HELD HIM BACK.
SO I BELIEVE FIRST OF ALL WE
NEED TO HAVE HEARINGS IN BOTH
THE HOUSE AND THE SENATE AND NOT
JUST WITH ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR.
WE NEED TO BRING DIRECTOR
MUELLER BEFORE THE UNITED STATES
SENATE, RIGHT?
BECAUSE OTHERWISE WE ARE NEVER
GOING TO GET TO THE BOTTOM OF
IT.
THE IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS ARE
UP TO THE HOUSE.
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO MAKE
THAT DECISION.
I AM IN THE SENATE, AND I
BELIEVE THAT WE ARE THE JURY.
I'VE ALWAYS BELIEVED THIS FROM
THE BEGINNING TO THE END.
I'M A FORMER PROSECUTOR.
I BELIEVE YOU LOOK AT THE
EVIDENCE TO MAKE DECISIONS.
SO IF THE HOUSE BRINGS THE
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS BEFORE
US, WE WILL DEAL WITH THEM.
BUT LET'S LOOK AT WHAT DIRECTOR
MUELLER SAID.
HE SAID THERE WERE TWO WAYS FOR
ACCOUNTABILITY.
ONE WAS DPCONGRESS, AND WE'RE
GOING TO START SEEING THAT WITH
THESE INVESTIGATIONS AND THE
SECOND IS OTHER INVESTIGATIONS,
RIGHT?
THERE'S CASES GOING ON IN YOUR
HOME STATE OF NEW YORK.
THERE'S CASES GOING ON ALL OVER
THE COUNTRY, BUT THERE IS A
THIRD WAY TO HOLD THIS PRESIDENT
ACCOUNTABLE AND THAT IS BY
DEFEATING HIM IN THE 2020
ELECTION.
AND I BELIEVE I CAN DO THAT.
>> SENATOR, JUST TO GIVE THEM A
QUICK SENSE, DO YOU BELIEVE THAT
ANYTHING YOU'VE READ AND
PROCESSED IN THAT REPORT COULD
HAVE THE WORD IMPEACHABLE
ATTACHED TO IT?
>> ANY -- FIRST OF ALL, I
BELIEVE I'M THE JURY HERE, SO
I'M NOT GOING TO PREDISPOSE
THINGS.
I'M NOT GOING TO SAY WHETHER IT
IS OR ISN'T.
BUT I WILL SAY THERE ARE VERY
DISTURBING THINGS THAT WOULD
LEAD YOU TO BELIEVE THERE'S
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
I ASKED ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR
THESE QUESTIONS.
I SAID, WELL, IF THE PRESIDENT
OR IF ANYONE WERE TO TRY TO
CHANGE THE TESTIMONY OF A
WITNESS WOULD YOU CONSIDER THAT
OBSTRUCTION?
I ASKED HIM A SERIES OF
QUESTIONS AND I'M REALLY LOOKING
FORWARD TO ASKING HIM THOSE
AGAIN BECAUSE SEVERAL OF THEM HE
ANSWERED YES AND SEVERAL OF THEM
HE WOULDN'T SAY.
AND A LOT OF THAT YOU SEE RIGHT
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE REPORT.
>> ALL RIGHT, NEXT QUESTION.
ELIJAH DEVON, SOPHOMORE AT
HARVARD FRUMP COMPTON,
CALIFORNIA.
HE INTERNED FOR SENATOR KAMALA
HARRIS LAST SUMMER BUT HE'S NOT
DECIDED WHICH CANDIDATE HE
SUPPORTS YET.
>> SENATOR, YOU'RE OFTEN
CRITICIZED FOR HAVING BEEN A
TOUGH ON CRIME PROSECUTOR WHO
TOOK PART IN THE WAR ON DRUGS
INCREASING YOUR COUNTY'S PRISON
POPULATION.
THESE PROSECUTIONS
DISPROPORTIONATELY AFFECTED
PEOPLE OF COLOR.
I PERSONALLY KNOW OF THESE
PLIGHTS AS MY FATHER MISSED THE
FIRST 13 YEARS OF HIS LIFE AS HE
WAS INCARCERATED FOR A
NONVIOLE DRUG RELATED OFFENSE.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO AS PRESIDENT
TO REMEDY THE TERRIBLE EFFECTS
OF THESE POLICIES?
>> I THINK AS YOU POINT OUT WHEN
YOU'RE IN A JOB LIKE I HAD, YOU
THINK ABOUT WHAT JUSTICE IS ALL
ABOUT.
AND I WOULD SAY ONE THING WE
SHOULD NOTE DURING MY TIME IN
THAT JOB WHERE I MANAGED THE
BIGGEST PROSECUTOR'S OFFICE IN
MY STATE WE ACTUALLY DID SEE
AFRICAN-AMERICAN INCARCERATION,
PRISON INCARCERATION GO DOWN BY
13%.
AND A LOT OF THAT WAS THAT WE
USED DRUG COURT AND WE TRIED TO
FIND OTHER WAYS TO GET JUSTICE
BECAUSE I ALWAYS LIKE TO SAY YOU
DON'T LIKE TO SEE REPEAT
CUSTOMERS WHEN YOU ARE IN THE
DA'S OFFICE.
AND ONE WAY YOU CAN ENSURE THAT
YOU DON'T IS BY GETTING THEM
TREATMENT.
SO I HAVE BEEN A BIG BELIEVER IN
DRUG COURTS AT THE STATE AND
FEDERAL LEVELS.
I'VE LED THAT EFFORT ON THE
FEDERAL LEVEL.
THE SECOND THING IS I THINK THAT
OUR OFFICES, BOTH POLICE
OFFICES, COUNTY ATTORNEY'S
OFFICES NEED TO REFLECT THE
POPULATION WE SERVE.
AND I WORK VERY HARD TO BRING
PEOPLE OF COLOR INTO OUR OFFICE,
AND WE WERE A LOT BETTER FOR IT.
AND A NUMBER OF THEM ROSE UP,
BIG SURPRISE, AND BECAME JUDGES.
THE OTHER THING IS THE WAY WE
HANDLED CASES WHEN THEY COME IN.
AND I WORKED WITH THE INNOCENCE
PROJECT WHEN I WAS IN THE DA NOT
ONLY TO REVIEW ALL OF OUR CASES
BUT BRING IN A NEW TYPE OF
EYEWITNESS I.D., SO INSTEAD OF
LOOKING AT EACH ONE, ONE AT A
TIME OR HAVING THEM ALL
TOGETHER, YOU WOULD LOOK AT EACH
PICTURE SO YOU'D HAVE TO MAKE AN
EVALUATION.
AND IT'S BEEN SHOWN TO DECREASE
OUR RACISM IN THE SYSTEM AND
DISCRIMINATORY DECISIONS BY
WITNESSES.
THE OTHER THING WE NEED TO DO IS
NOT JUST PASS THE FIRST STEP
ACT, AND I WAS PROUD TO BE A
COSPONSOR OF THAT LEGISLATION
WHICH WILL FINALLY REDUCE THE
NONVIOLENT DRUG SENTENCES LIKE
YOUR DAD HAD HAD WITH, BUT WOULD
HELP US TO SAY THE REST OF THE
COUNTRY, HEY, 90% OF THE PEOPLE
INCARCERATED ARE INCARCERATED IN
OUR STATE AND LOCAL JAILS.
O DOING SOMETHING ON THE FEDERAL
LEVEL IS GOOD, BUT WE HAVE TO
CREATE INCENTIVES TO BRING THOSE
SENTENCES DOWN AS WELL ON THE
STATE AND LOCAL LEVEL.
THERE IS RACISM IN OUR CRIMINAL
JUSTICE SYSTEM.
THERE HAS BEEN RACISM IN OUR
CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM FOR A
LONG TIME, AND WE MUST PLEDGE TO
FIX IT.
ONE LAST THING, I PUT OUT A PLAN
FOR A CLEMENCY BOARD, SO WHEN
I'M PRESIDENT, YES, I WANT TO
HEAR FROM THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
ON WHAT THEIR VIEWS ARE WHEN YOU
LOOK AT PARDONS.
BUT I ALSO WANT TO HEAR FROM A
GROUP FROM THE OUTSIDE THAT'S
GOING TO LOOK AT THESE CASES.
BECAUSE WHEN YOU SEE SOME OF THE
CASES LIKE A WOMAN THAT
PRESIDENT OBAMA PARDONED NAMED
J
JOSEFINE SHE LITERALLY SERVED 24
YEARS.
SHE HADN'T SOLD THE DRUGS
HERSELF, SHE DIDN'T DO THE
DRUGS.
SHE WAS A MIDDLE PERSON.
WE DON'T WANT TO SEE MORE OUT
THERE.
WE WANT TO HAVE A JUSTICE SYSTEM
THAT'S JUST.
>> THAT TAKES US TO OUR NEXT
QUESTION.
MAX WINEBERG, STUDIED POLITICAL
SCIENCE, HE'S FROM NEW YORK.
>> HI, SENATOR.
THERE ARE MANY CANDIDATES THAT
SUPPORT FREE COLLEGE AND STUDENT
LOAN FORGIVENESS.
YOU HAVE STATED THAT YOU'RE NOT
FOR EITHER OF THOSE.
AS A CURRENT COLLEGE STUDENT
ABOUT TO GRADUATE WITH A LOT OF
DEBT, WHY SHOULD I VOTE FOR YOU?
>> OKAY, BECAUSE I ACTUALLY WANT
TO GET SOMETHING DONE WHEN IT
COMES TO STUDENT LOANS.
I'VE HAD MY OWN STUDENT LOANS
WHEN I MET MY HUSBAND AND HE HAD
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF STUDENT
LOANS.
GOOD NEWS FOR YOU GUYS, I
MARRIED HIM ANYWAY.
AND I HAVE SEEN THE IMPACT OF
STUDENT LOANS.
SO HERE'S MY IDEA.
LET ME PUT IT OUT THERE.
FIRST OF ALL, YOU HAVE GOT
$1.5 TRILLION OF STUDENT DEBT
RIGHT NOW IN THIS COUNTRY, A LOT
OF HOME MORTGAGE DEBT, A LOT OF
CREDIT CARD DEBT.
OUR GOVERNMENT ALSO HAS A LOT OF
DEBT.
SO THE FIRST THING I WOULD DO IS
ALLOW STUDENTS AND NO MATTER HOW
OLD THEY ARE, FORMER STUN TO
REFINANCE THEIR STUDENT LOANS AT
THAT RATE THAT'S A LITTLE ABOVE
3%, WE COULD EVEN GO LOWER TO
FIND SOME EVEN BETTER RATE THAN
THAT.
BUT THAT'S WHAT I THINK WE NEED
TO DO TO BRING THE INTEREST RATE
PAYMENTS DOWN FOR THOSE
AMERICANS THAT STILL HAVE THE
STUDENT LOANS.
THE SECOND THING I WOULD DO IS
EXPAND PROGRAMS AND MAKE IT
EASIER FOR PEOPLE DEPENDING ON
YOUR INCOME LEVEL TO MAKE THAT
EASIER AS WELL AS THE AMOUNT OF
MONEY YOU GET.
THE THIRD THING I DO IS BRING
BACK PRESIDENT OBAMA'S PLAN FOR
FREE COMMUNITY COLLEGE.
THOSE ARE TWO YEAR DEGREES, AND
THAT GETS A LOT OF STUDENTS A
GOOD START.
MY OWN SISTER DIDN'T GRADUATE
FROM HIGH SCHOOL.
SHE HAD A HARD TIME THEN, AND
SHE WENT AND WORKED IN
MANUFACTURING AND THEN SHE LATER
WENT AND GOT HER GED, AND THEN
AFTER THAT SHE WENT TO COMMUNITY
COLLEGE AND SHE GOT HER DEGREE
THERE.
IT TOOK YEARS, AND AFTER THAT
SHE FINISHED HER FOUR YEAR
DEGREE AND IS NOW GAINFULLY
EMPLOYED.
THERE ARE A LOT OF PATHS TO
SUCCESS IN AMERICA, BUT WE CAN
ALL AGREE THAT WE WANT TO MAKE
CLE
COLLEGE MORE AFFORDABLE.
WE LOOK AT ALSO THERE'S LOAN
FORGIVENESS.
I HOPE YOU FOLLOW A LOT OF
PEOPLE THAT GO ON THIS PATH
OF --
>> LIKE SENATOR WARREN.
>> -- PUBLIC SERVICE.
RIGHT.
I THINK WE CAN ALSO EXPAND THAT
INTO IN DEMAND JOBS.
SO IT LOOK LIKE YOU HAVE A
FOLLOW-UP, CHRIS.
>> I WAS LISTENING AND THIS IS
THE AUDIENCE TO HAVE THIS
CONVERSATION WITH.
SO MANY OF THESE KIDS YOU'RE
GOING TO SEE SIX FIGURES IN DEBT
BEFORE SIX FIGURES IN SALARY.
SENATOR WARREN SAYS WE'LL
FORGIVE THE DEBT.
WE'LL FORGIVE UP TO $50,000.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF LOAN
FORGIVENESS AND PLANS THAT ARE
MORE GENEROUS ON THE OUTSIDE
THAN YOUR OWN?
>> WELL, I WOULD TARGET THE LOAN
FORGIVENESS AT THOSE THAT, FOR
INSTANCE -- I PROTUPBROUGHT UP
THAT WENT INTO PUBLIC SERVICE,
IN DEMAND JOBS WE HAVE IN OUR
ECONOMY.■■■■SH I COULD STAPLE■■E
COLLEGE DIPLOMA UNDER EVERY ONE
OF YOUR CHAIRS.
I DON'T.
DON'T LOOK.
IT'S NOT THERE.
I WISH I COULD DO THAT BUT I
HAVE TO BE STRAIGHT WITH YOU AND
TELL YOU THE TRUTH AND THAT IS
YOUR GENERATION IS AN INCREDIBLE
GENERATION.
THEY SAY KIDS YOUR AGE LIVE IN
THEIR PARENTS BASEMENT MORE THAN
ANY OTHER GENERATION.
IS THAT YOUR CHOICE?
NO.
IT'S BECAUSE WE HAVE SADDLED YOU
WITH A BUNCH OF DEBT, WITH JOBS
THAT OFTEN DON'T HAVE BENEFITS
WITH THEM, ALL RIGHT?
THEY SAY CRAZY THINGS ABOUT YOUR
GENERATION.
SOME OF MY FAVORITE ONES ARE
THAT YOU HAVE CONTRIBUTED TO
GETTING RID OF PAPER NAPKINS.
OKAY, THAT'S SMART BECAUSE YOU
CHOSE TO USE PAPER TOWELS, ALL
RIGHT?
OR THEY HAVE SAID THAT YOUR
GENERATION IS GID OF
DIAMOND RINGS.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE YOU HAVE
TOO MUCH STUDENT DEBT, ALL
RIGHT?
AND SO YOU GO THROUGH ALL THESE
THINGS AND WHAT I SEE IN YOUR
GENERATION IS THE LEAST RACIST
GENERATION WE'VE EVER HAD IN
THIS COUNTRY.
IT IS THE MOST DIVERSE
GENERATION WE'VE EVER HAD IN
THIS COUNTRY.
IT IS A GENERATION THAT CARES
MO ABOUT THE WORLD AROUND THEM
THAN WE EVER HAVE HAD IN THIS
COUNTRY.
SO YOU DESERVE MORE THAN TO BE
SADDLED WITH MORE AND MORE DEBT,
ALL RIGHT?
SO EVERYTHING THAT I HAVE
PROPOSED TO YOU, I HAVE FOUND
WAYS TO PAY FOR IT THAT I THINK
MAKES SENSE THAT WE CAN ACTUALLY
GET DONE.
WE CAN REPEAL REGRESSIVE
PORTIONS OF OF THAT TRUMP TAX
CUT WHERE SO MUCH OF THE MONEY
WENT TO THE TOP.
WE CAN CHANGE THE WAY WE HANDLED
SOMETHING CALLED THE CARRIED
INTEREST LOOPHOLE WHERE HEDGE
FUND MANAGERS GET TO HAVE THEIR
TAXES AT LESS OF A RATE THAN
ANYONE ELSE.
WE CAN CHANGE THE WAY WE DO
CAPITAL GAINS TAX WHICH IS
ANOTHER WAY WE COULD LITERALLY
BRING IN HUNDREDS OF BILLIONS OF
DOLLARS.
THOSE ARE WAYS WE CAN PAY TO
MAKE SURE THAT EVERYONE CAN
AFFORD COLLEGE.
BECAUSE ONE SIZE DOESN'T FIT ■W.
JENNIFER'S A SOPHOMORE AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF NEW HAMPSHIRE
STUDYING POLITICAL SCIENCE AND
HISTORY, HAS A QUESTION ABOUT
THE WAGE GAP.
>> HI, SENATOR.
A MAN WHO IS EQUALLY OR LESSER
QUALIFIED THAN I AM WILL
AUTOMATICALLY MAKE MORE MONEY
THAN ME.
SO MY QUESTION IS WHAT WILL YOU
DO TO CLOSE THE WAGE GAP?
>> PASS THE EQUAL PAY ACT, THAT
WOULD BE ONE THING.
WE'VE ALREADY PASSED THE ACT
THAT WE WERE PROUD OF THAT MADE
IT EASIER FOR WOMEN TO CONTEST
THESE KINDS OF CASES WHEN
THEY'RE IN THE WORKPLACE.
I THINK ALSO MAKING IT EASIER
FOR WOMEN TO GET THE KIND OF
JOBS THEY SHOULD.
I WOULD LOVE TO PASS THE ERA,
RIGHT, GET THAT CEMENTED INTO
LAW ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
AND THEN MAKE SURE WE HAVE ROLE
MODELS ACROSS IT COUNTRY.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW THAT MOVIE,
HIDDIAN FIGURES I LOVE THAT
MOVIE.
BUT WOMEN LEADERS,
AFRICAN-AMERICAN WOMEN
ESPECIALLY SHOULDN'T BE HIDDEN
FIGURES ANYMORE.
THEY SHOULD BE REAL LEADERS IN
THE BOARDROOM, LEADERS IN THE
U.S. SENATE LIKE WE'RE ALREADY
STARTING TO SEE AND THEY SHOULD
BE LEADERS IN THE WHITE HOUSE.
AND WHEN YOU HAVE A WOMAN
PRESIDENT, I HAVE A FUNNY
FEELING WE'RE FINALLY GOING TO
GET CHILD CARE POLICY DONE IN
THIS COUNTRY, RIGHT?
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE THE KIND OF
CHANGES WE WANT TO SEE TO MAKE
IT EASIER FOR WORKING FAMILIES
AND FOR EVERYONE TO ACHIEVE
THINGS.
BECAUSE OTHERWISE OUR ECONOMY IS
GOING TO BE STAGNANT IF EVERYONE
CAN'T HAVE A SEAT AT THE TABLE.
BECAUSE THE OLD JOKE WE USED TO
SAY FOR WOMEN CANDIDATES IS IF
YOU'RE NOT AT THE TABLE, YOU'RE
ON THE MENU.
SO THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPEN.
>> ALL RIGHT, AND ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT APPLIES MOST EVENLY
ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND NO MATTER
WHAT YOU MAKE, HEALTH CARE.
GRAHAM MACKLAND, ST. STUDYING
ECONOMICS, HE'S FROM
MASSACHUSETTS.
WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION?
>> THANK YOU, SENATOR.
IN A PERFECT WORLD WHICH
COUNTRY'S HEALTH CARE SYSTEM
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE THE U.S.'
MOST CLOSELY RESEMBLE AND WHAT
SPECIFIC POLICIES DO YOU HOPE TO
TAKE IN THAT DIRECTION?
>> OKAY, WELL I'M NOT GOING TO
PICK A PARTICULAR COUNTRY JUST
BECAUSE I THINK OUR COUNTRY CAN
BE THE BEST IF WE MAKE SOME
CHANGES.
BUT THERE SHOULD BE SOME MODELS
WE COMBINE TO MAKE OUR SYSTEM
BETTER.
LET ME TALK AT WE NEED
TO DO IN AMERICA AS OPPOSED TO
SOME OTHER COUNTRY THAT MIGHT
NOT FIT OUR SITUATION.
I THINK FIRST OF ALL WE NEED TO
BRING DOWN PREMIUMS.
I NOTE ON THE AFFORDABLE CARE
ACT SIDE FOR YOUNG PEOPLE, IT'S
HAD A MAJOR IMPACT.
ONE, YOU CAN KEEP ON YOUR
PARENTS INSURANCE UNTIL YOU'RE
26, RIGHT?
TWO, WE'VE SEEN HALF OF THE
YOUNG PEOPLE WHO ARE UNINSURED,
THEY'VE BECOME INSURED BECAUSE
OF THE AFFORDABLE CARE ACT,
WHICH IS A BIG DEAL.
AND THREE, ONE OUT OF SIX OF YOU
ACTUALLY HAVE PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS.
SO IF WE GET RID OF THE
AFFORDABLE CARE ACT, WHICH IS
WHAT THIS PRESIDENT IS TRYING TO
DO, ALL OF THOSE BENEFITS WILL
GO AWAY.
SO MY FIRST FOCUS IS MAKING SURE
WE KEEP THAT IN PLACE BUT WE
IMPROVE IT BY BRINGING PREMIUMS
DOWN.
YOU CAN DO THAT MANY WAYS.
ONE OF MY MAJOR PROPOSALS IS TO
BRING BACK THE PUBLIC OPTIONS
IDEA THAT'S BEEN FLOATING AROUND
THAT SHOULD HAVE BEEN PUT IN THE
FIRST PLACE.
YOU CAN DO IT WITH MEDICAID OR
MEDICARE SO YOU HAVE A LESS
EXPENSIVE OPTION TO PICK FROM.
THE OTHER THING I WOULD DO IS TO
BRING DOWN THE COST OF
PHARMACEUTICALS.
EVERYONE IN THIS AUDITORIUM HERE
KNOWS SOMEONE THAT'S BEEN HURT
BY THE HIGH COSTS OF
PRESCRIPTION DRUGS.
MY OWN DAUGHTER HAS ALLERGIES
AND SHE CARRIES AN EPIPEN
EVERYWHERE SHE WENT.
SO WHEN I SAW THAT COST DRUBL,
TRIPLE LIKE WE SAW A FEW YEARS
BACK I TOOK IT ON.
I TOOK IT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, THE
STATE FAIR BOOTH AND TV, AND WE
WON THAT FIGHT.
BUT NOT EVERY FAMILY IS GOING TO
BE ABLE TO TAKE ON EVERY SINGLE
PRICE INCREASE.
WE NEED COMPETITION BY HAVING
NEGOTIATION FOR MEDICARE PRICE,
YOU MIGHT THINK IT DOESN'T
AFFECT ME BECAUSE I'M NOT ON
MEDICARE.
GUESS WHAT?
THAT'LL BRING DOWN THE PRICES
FOR EVERYONE.
WE SHOULD BRING IN LESS
EXPENSIVE DRUGS FROM OTHER
COUNTRIES LIKE CANADA.
WE CAN PRACTICALLY SEE CANADA
FROM OUR PORTS WHEN WE'RE UP
HERE, RIGHT, AND THEY HAVE LESS
EXPENSIVE DRUG PRICES THAN WE
HAVE IN AMERICA.
WE CAN STOP THIS HORRIBLE
PRACTICE WHERE BIG
PHARMACEUTICALS PAY OFF, THEY
LITERALLY PAY OFF GENERICS TO
KEEP THE PRICES AND COMPETITION
OFF THE MARKET.
THAT'S BAD, AND WE CAN FICK
THIS.
>> THIS IS ONE OF THE
DISTINGUISHING ISSUES TONIGHT TO
DISCUSS ESPECIALLY WITH YOU,
SENATOR.
BECAUSE YOU'RE THE ONLY SENATOR
TONIGHT WHO IS NOT COSPONSORING
THE NEW MEDICARE FOR ALL BILL.
AND I WANTED TO PUT THAT IN THE
CONTEXT OF SOMETHING WE LEARNED
FROM OUR PARTNERSHIP.
THE YOUTH POLL SAYS THAT THE
MAJORITY OF LIKELY YOUNG VOTERS
ARE FOR IT.
SO THIS AUDIENCE, 52% OF THE
LIKELY VOTERS HERE FOR MEDICARE
FOR ALL.
YOU'RE NOT.
WHAT'S YOUR SELL?
>> OKAY, LET ME GO.
SO I WANT TO BRING DOWN YOUR
HEALTH CARE COSTS.
I THINK I'VE EXPLAINED THAT, AND
I THINK YOU'VE GOT TO BELIEVE ME
ON THIS.
I HAVE BEEN OUT FRONT TAKING ON
THE PHARMACEUTICAL COMPANIES AND
WAS OUT FRONT AS AN ADVOCATE FOR
THE AFFORDABLE CARE ACT FROM THE
VERY BEGINNING.
BUT I WANT TO GET TO UNIVERSAL
HEALTH CARE AND I MEANT TO GET
THEIR FAST.
AND ONE OF THE WAYS WE DO THAT
IS FIRST OF ALL WE CAN
IMMEDIATELY DO SOMETHING TO
BRING DOWN THOSE PREMIUM PRICES
WITH SOMETHING I'M NOT GOING TO
GO INTO BUT IT'S COST SHARING AS
WELL AS RESHOOURS.
BUT THEN THE NEXT BIG THING IS
GET THAT PUBLIC OPTION IN PLACE.
THEN YOU DON'T HAVE MIDDLE MEN.
YOU HAVE COMPETITION, YOU HAVE
PEOPLE THAT WILL GO EVER THERE
AND I BELIEVE ONCE YOU HAVE THAT
SETUP IN THE RIGHT WAY WHICH IS
WHY THE INSURANCE COMPANIES WERE
FIGHTING AGAINST IT, AND THAT IS
THE WAY YOU GET THERE WITHOUT
SUDDENLY DISMANTLE THE ENTIRE
SYSTEM WHICH WAS VERY DIFFICULT
TO DO WHEN WE PUT THE AFFORDABLE
CARE ACT IN PLACE.
YOU GUYS WERE PRETTY YOUNG, IT
WAS A FEW YEARS AGO BUT IT WAS A
HARD THING TO DO.
AND WHAT I WANT TO DO IS WHAT DO
THE DOCTORS SAY?
DO NO HARM.
AND I THINK WE DO NO HARM AND DO
US MUCH BETTER BY GETTING THAT
PUBLIC OPTION IN PLACE.
AND NO ONE HAS TAKEN ON
PHARMACEUTICAL COMPANIES.
YOU ALL KNOW SOMEONE THAT HAS
DIABETES, SOMEONE STRUGGLING
WITH THAT COST OF INSULIN.
WE HAD A GUY IN MY STATE WHO'S A
RESTAURANT MANAGER WHO'S 26
YEARS OLD WHO WAS ON HIS MOM'S
HEALTH INSURANCE.
AND THEN WHEN HE HAD TO GET OFF
IT, HE COULDN'T AFFORD IT, HE
STARTED RATIONING AND HE DIED.
THAT HAPPENED IN OUR COUNTRY.
SO IF WE KEEP PUTTING IN
PRESIDENTS LIKE THIS ONE WHO
BASICALLY HAS SAID HE WANTS TO
DO SOMETHING ABOUT PHARMA AND
THEN HE PUTS HIS PLAN OUT AND
THE STOCK GOES UP, THAT ACTUALLY
HAPPENED, OKAY.
WHAT WE NEED TO DO IS PUT
SOMEONE IN WHO HAS■7■7 TRACK
RECORD OF TAKING ON PHARMA WHO'S
WILLING TO GET IT DONE AND
ACTUALLY HAS A TRACK RECORD OF
PASSING BILLS AND WORKING ACROSS
THE AISLE ESPECIALLY ON
PHARMACEUTICALS TO GET IT DONE.
I'M THAT PERSON.
>> WELL, THAT'S A GOOD SEGWAY
BECAUSE THE POLICY IDEAS ARE
ONLY AS GOOD AS YOUR IDEAS TO
PUT THEM INTO PRACTICE.
ADEN PIERCE STUDYING
INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS FROM
MASSACHUSETTS.
HE'S GOT A QUESTION ABOUT HOW
YOU WIN WITH A SPECIFIC GROUP.
>> THANK YOU, SENATOR, FOR
TAKING MY QUESTION.
DONALD TRUMP WON THE 2016
ELECTION IN LARGE PART BECAUSE
HE APPEALED TO A DISCONTENT
MIDDLE CLASS IN THE HEARTLAND.
HOW DO YOU WIN BACK THEIR TRUST
AND THEIR VOTE?
>> I GUESS YOU LOOK AT WHAT I'VE
DONE, AND I AM SOMEONE THAT RUNS
IN A PURPLE STATE.
IT IS A STATE WHEN I FIRST
STARTED RUNNING FOR OFFICE THE
OTHER SENATOR WAS REPUBLICAN,
THE GOVERNOR WAS REPUBLICAN AND
THREE OUR FOUR OF OUR OFFICES
WAS REPUBLICAN.
AND I STARTED RUNNING.
AND EVERY SINGLE TIME I HAVE WON
I HAVE WON EVERY SINGLE
CONGRESSIONAL DISTRICT IN MY
STATE.
IT'S WHEN YOU GUYS ARE SUPPOSED
TO CHEER, OKAY?
AND I DIDN'T DO THAT BY SELLING
OUT ON MY PRINCIPLES.
I DID THAT BY GOING NOT JUST
WHERE IT'S COMFORTABLE BUT WHERE
IT'S UNCOMFORTABLE.
I DID THAT BY MEETING PEOPLE
WHERE THEY WERE.
BY GOING TO FARMS, GOING TO
SMALL TOWN CAVES, BY WINNING THE
RIGHT WAY.
AND THEY DIDN'T AGREE WITH
EVERYTHING I'VE SAID AND THEY
STILL DON'T, BUT THEY TRUSTED
ME.
THEY TRUSTED ME WITH THEIR
MONEY, THEIR IDEAS AND THEY
TRUSTED I WAS GOING TO GO TO
WASHINGTON TO HAVE THEIR BACK.
AND I THINK WE NEED THAT KIND OF
MESSAGE, WE NEED THAT KIND OF
MESSENGER IF WE'RE GOING TO WIN
THIS.
AND JUST LAST ELECTION IN 2018
DONALD TRUMP IS GOING TO WIN OUR
STATE.
I CAME BACK TWO YEARS LATER AND
WON 40 OF THE RURAL COUNTIES
THAT HE WON.
I THINK THAT IT IS NOT JUST THE
MIDDLE OF THE COUNTRY, IT'S
REALLY THE ENTIRE MIDDLE CLASS
ACROSS THE COUNTRY THAT WE HAVE
TO HAVE POLICIES AND IDEAS AND
BREAD AND BUTTER IDEAS THAT SHOW
WE HAVE THEIR BACK.
AND IT DOESN'T MATTER THE COLOR
OF ANYONE'S SKIN.
IF WE NEED TO SHOW WE HAVE THEIR
BACK.
AND THE PROBLEM IS THAT MESSAGE
GOT LOST BECAUSE DONALD TRUMP
LIKES TO DIVERT YOU EVERY SINGLE
DAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT HE DOES.
HE SENDS OUT A TWEET TO TRY TO
CONTROL THE MESSAGE.
WHEN HE DID THAT TO ME AND I
ANNOUNCED MY CANDIDACY IN THE
MIDDLE OF A BLIZZARD AND HE MADE
FUN OF ME FOR TALKING ABOUT
CLIMATE CHANGE -- BY THE WAY,
HAPPY EARTH DAY.
WHEN HE MADE FUN OF ME FOR DOING
THAT, I SAID, HEY, DONALD TRUMP,
THE SCIENCE IT ON MY SIDE.
AND I'D LIKE TO SEE HOW YOUR
HAIR WOULD FAIR IN A BLIZZARD.
SO THE POINT HERE IS THAT, YES,
WHAT HAPPENED IN 2016 WE HAD A
GREAT CANDIDATE WITH GREAT
POLICIES.
WE HAD RUSSIA COMING IN AND
INVADING OUR ELECTION.
AND BY THE WAY, I DON'T CARE IF
THEY DID IT WITH TANKS OR
MISSILES AND THIS TIME THEY DID
IT TO OUR ELECTION.
WE HAD NEVER RUN AGAINST ANYONE
LIKE DONALD TRUMP.
WELL, WE LEARNED HOW TO DO THAT
IN 2018.
AND SOMETIMES, YES, STANDING
YOUR GROUND IN YOUR VALUES,
SOMETIMES IGNORING HIM AND
SOMETIMES USING A LITTLE HUMOR.
BECAUSE A LOT OF THE THINGS HE
SAYS ARE JUST COMPLETELY ABSURD,
AND WE NEED TO TAKE IT TO THE
PEOPLE IN MINNESOTA AND
WISCONSIN AND ACROSS THE COUNTRY
AND THAT'S HOW WE WIN THIS
ELECTION.
>> LET'S TAKE A QUICK BREAK.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH CNN'S
SPECIAL PRESIDENTIAL TOWN HALL
EVENT FROM MANCHESTER, NEW
HAMPSHIRE.
STAY WITH CNN.
Or NEW Colossal Shrimp & Salmon
with a citrusy drizzle.
Tender, smoky, and together
on one plank...
...but not for long-
so hurry in!
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it
from your allergy pills?
Flonase relieves
your worst symptoms
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
Flonase helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances.
Most pills only block one.
Flonase.
There's brushing...and
there's Oral-B Power brushing.
Oral-B just cleans better.
Even my hygienist said
going electric could lead to way
cleaner teeth.
And unlike Sonicare,
Oral-B is the first electric
toothbrush brand
accepted by the ADA.
Oral-B.
This is not a bed...
it's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed, from $999...
senses your movement and
automatically adjusts
on each side to keep
you both comfortable.
And snoring?
How smart is that?
Smarter sleep.
So you can come out swinging,
maintain your inner
focus, and wake up rested
and ready for anything.
And now, save $400 on select
Sleep Number 360 smart beds.
Plus, free premium delivery
when you add a base.
Ends Saturday.
>>> ALL RIGHT, WELCOME BACK TO
CNN'S SPECIAL DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL TOWN HALL, AND
THAT'S WITH MINNESOTA SENATOR
AMY KLOBUCHAR, THE FIRST OF FIVE
PRESIDENTIAL TOWN HALLS TONIGHT.
WE ARE JUST GETTING STARTED.
WHAT A RANGE OF GREAT QUESTIONS
IN THAT FIRST UND.
I  WE'LL MATCH IT BETTER
THIS TIME.
START WITH THOMAS.
A SOPHOMORE FROM HARVARD AT
RHODE ISLAND.
YOUR QUESTION IS ABOUT FROZEN
PIZZA.
>> IT IS.
HI, SENATOR.
IN 2010 YOU PETITIONED THE UDA
TO KEEP FROZEN PIZZAS IN
LUNCHES.
AMID THE OBESITY EPIDEMIC THAT
HAS PLAGUED THIS COUNTRY FOR
DECADES TO WHAT EXTENT DO YOU
BELIEVE THE FINANCIAL CORPORATE
INTERESTS IN THIS STATE SHOULD
OUTWEIGH?
>> FIRST OF ALL, I MADE CLEAR IN
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" ARTICLE A
FEW YEARS LATER WHEN I ASKED
ABOUT THAT IS IT WAS JUST A
LETTER I HAD SENT.
WE WERE IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
DOWNTURN, AND IT WAS A LITTLE
MORE I WOULD SAY COMPLEX IN
TERMS OF THE LANGUAGE, BUT IT'S
A FAIR CRITICISM.
AND SO I SAID I REGRETTED
SENDING THAT LETTER.
IT WAS ABOUT TRYING TO KEEP A
COMPANY AFLOAT IN A REALLY SMALL
TOWN THAT EMPLOYED A BUNCH OF
PEOPLE.
PUT I THINK THAT NUTRITION IS
PARAMOUNT TO THIS COUNTRY, AND
THAT'S WHY WAY BEFORE I WAS
RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT I SAID
THAT WAS A MISTAKE, ALL RIGHT?
SO LET'S TALK ABOUT THE BIGGER
ISSUE WHICH IS NUTRITION, AND
THAT IS THAT WE NEED TO HAVE
HEALTHIER FOODS IN KIDS'
LUNCHES.
WE NEED TO HAVE HEALTHIER FOODS
AVAILABLE NO MATTER HOW MUCH
THEY ARE.
AND AS R I HAVE BEEN A MAJOR
ADVOCATE FOR BETTER SCHOOL
LUNCH, MORE NUTRITIOUS SCHOOL
LUNCHES.
I ALSO HAD A BILL FOR PRESCHOOL
SCHOOL LUNCHES TO MAKE SURE
THOSE ARE NUTRITIOUS AS WELL.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN IN THE
CONTEXT -- THIS WOULD BE
UNPOPULAR WITH THIS CROWD.
>> THIS IS ABOUT HOW IT WAS
COUNTED.
NO, I DIDN'T THINK THAT FROZEN
PIZZA WITH TOMATO SAUCE ON IT, I
DO NOT BELIEVE SHOULD BE COUNTED
AS A VEGETABLE.
>> BUT SHOULD IT BE IN LUNCHES?
>> I THINK THAT IS SOMETIMES IN
LUNCHES.
>> BUT SHOULD IT BE?
>>LONG AS YE OTHER
THINGS WITH IT, RIGHT?
AS LONG AS YOU HAVE REAL
VEGETABLES WITH IT, AND AS LONG
AS YOU HAVE OTHER THINGS WITH
IT.
AND I'M LOOKING AT MY DAUGHTER
RIGHT NOW -- BY THE WAY, SHE IS
HERE.
SHE IS 23 AND PLEASE BE NICE TO
HER BECAUSE HOW WOULD YOU FEEL
IF IT WAS YOUR MOM UP HERE BEING
ASKED ABOUT PIZZA.
>> CALLING HER OUT IN FRONT OF
EVERYBODY.
>> THERE SHE IS.
EXACTLY, EXACTLY.
SHE WENT TO A SCHOOL ACTUALLY
THAT'S A LITTLE DIFFERENT THAN
YOUR SCHOOL.
AND HER SCHOOL WAS I THINK IN
HIGH SCHOOL IT WAS IN MIDDLE
WHERE SOMETHING LIKE 90% FREE
AND REDUCED LUNCH, MAYBE EVEN A
LITTLE HIGHER THAN THAT.
AND THAT WAS A SCHOOL IN
MINNEAPOLIS SHE WENT FOR SEVERAL
YEARS AND I GET TO BE IN THE
LUNCHROOM AND SAW WHAT IT WAS
LIKE FOR THESE KIDS THAT
COULDN'T AFFORD LUNCH.
I THINK EVERYONE IN HER CLASS AT
ONE POINT WAS AN IMMIGRANT
EXCEPT HER.
AND THERE WERE KIDS IN THE
LUNCHROOMS THAT WERE TREEING TO
GET STUFF BUT THEY WOULD GET A
DOUGHNUT AND EAT THAT INSTEAD.
A LOT OF THE KIDS WERE GETTING
STUFF OUT OF THE VENDING
MACHINES TO BRING HOME AND EAT
FOR DINNER.
I KNOW BECAUSE MY DAUGHTER ONLY
WENT TO PUBLIC SCHOOL AND FOR A
NUMBER OF YEARS SHE WENT TO
PUBLIC SCHOOLS WHERE THE VAST
MAJORITY WERE FREE AND REDUCED
LUNCH.
YOU ASKED ME WHERE THIS COMES
FROM AND WHY I BROUGHT IT UP
BECAUSE I'VE LIVED IT.
>> OUR NEXT QUESTION IS FROM
ADRIANA FERNANDES, A SOPHOMORE
AND ORIGINALLY FROM NICARAGUA.
>> MY QUESTION IS OUR CURRENT
SECRETARY OF EDUCATION IS
ATTEMPTING TO SLASH FUNDING FROM
SPECIAL NEEDS PROGRAMS.
WHAT ARE YOUR IDEAS REGARDING
THE FEDERAL RESPONSIBILITY TO
THE EDUCATION SYSTEM?
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, AND LET'S
MENTION THE NAME OF THAT
EDUCATION SECRETARY IS BETSEY
DeVOS, OKAY?
SOMEONE THAT I STRONGLY OPPOSED
AND I JUST THINK SHOULDN'T BE IN
HER JOB.
AND SO IT IS NO■■■ SURPRISE TO
ME -- IT IS NO SURPRISE TO ME
THESE THINGS KEEP HAPPENING, AND
SHE NOT ONLY HAS TRIED TO DEFUND
SPECIAL EDUCATION, BUT SHE ALSO
HAS TRIED TO GET RID OF THE
SPECIAL OLYMPICS FUNDING, IF YOU
WATCHED ANY OF THIS.
AND I THINK WE NOTED THAT
LITERALLY JUST A FEW TRIPS BACK
TO MAR-A-LAGO AND BACK WITH THE
PRESIDENT COULD HAVE FUNTHE
SPECIAL OLYMPICS FUNDING.
THAT IS TRUE STATISTIC.
SO I THINK OUR JOB IN GOVERNMENT
IS TO REPRESENT EVERYONE, AND IT
IS PARTICULAR TO REPRESENT
PEOPLE THAT MAYBE CAN'T WRITE A
CHECK THEMSELVES, RIGHT?
OR MAYBE CAN'T EVEN WRITE
THEMSELVES OR MAYBE NEED HELP?
MAYBE THEY'RE IN A WHEELCHAIR.
MAYBE THEY HAVE PHYSICAL
DISABILITIES, MAYBE MENTAL
DISABILITIES, BUT OUR JOB IS TO
STANDBY THEM.
I REMEMBER BEING IN A SMALL TOWN
PARADE IN MINNESOTA A FEW YEARS
AGO AND A MOM WAS PUSHING A BABY
CARRIAGE AND SHE POINTED AT A
DAWDLER AND SHE SAID THIS IS MY
BOY, HE'S ONLY 3 YEARS OLD AND
HAS DOWN STREAM.
THIS IS WHAT A PRE-EXISTING
CONDITION LOOKS LIKE.
AND THAT WAS THE MOMENT I SAID
TO MYSELF FINALLY PEOPLE KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS.
IT MEANS THINGS LIKE
DISABILITIES.
IT MEANS THINGS LIKE IF YOU'RE A
VICTIM OF DOMESTIC VIOLENCE.
IF MEANS THINGS LIKE IF YOU HAVE
DIABETES OR YOU HAVE CANCER OR
YOUR MOM HAS A CERTAIN DISEASE.
SO WE NOT ONLY NEED TO STAND UP
WHEN IT COMES TO DISABILITY
FUNDING INCLUDING EDUCATION
FUNDING WITH IDEA, BUT IT IS THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT PUTTING
MANDATES ON THE STATE AND THEN
NOT PUTTING THE MONEY WITH IT.
BUT WE ALSO NEED TO STAND UP
WHEN IT COMES TO HEALTH CARE FOR
PEOPLE WITH DISABILITIES.
AND WHEN YOU CHECK THESE THINGS
OFF WITH WHAT THIS
ADMINISTRATION HAS DONE, THEY
WANT TO GET RID OF THE
AFFORDABLE CARE ACT AND THOSE
PROTECTIONS.
THAT HURTS THE DISABILITY
COMMUNITY.
THEY WANT TO REDUCE THE FUNDING
FOR SPECIAL ED AND FOR THE
OLYMPICS WHICH THEN HAD A
REVERSE ON BECAUSE THERE WAS
SUCH A PUBLIC OUTCRY.
THAT HURTS PEOPLE WITH
DISABILITIES, AND THEY HAVEN'T
DONE ANYTHING TO FUND EDUCATION
FOR PEOPLE WITH DISABILITIES.
SO I GIVE THEM SINCE YOU'RE ALL
STUDENTS, AN "F."
>> ON THAT ISSUE OF CLIMATE I
WANT TO BRING IN MADELEINE
WOODS, A SENIOR AT HARVARD.
>> HELLO, MADELEINE AND
CONGRATULATIONS ON THAT.
>> THANK YOU.
I DON'T HAVE MUCH CHOICE IN IT
BUT IT WAS A GREAT CHILDHOOD.
SPEAKING OF THE CLIMATE, YOU
BACKED ALEXANDRIA
OCASIO-CORTEZ'S GREEN NEW DEAL.
WHILE I WAS RAISED IN A WOLF
SANCTUARY I COME FROM A RURAL
ISOLATED TOWN WHERE PEOPLE
CRITICIZED THE GREEN NEW DEAL
AND FOUND IT LAUGHABLE THAT THEY
WERE BEING TOLD HOW TO CARE FOR
THEIR ENVIRONMENT BY PEOPLE FROM
LARGE CITIES.
SO I KNOW YOU HAVE A LOT OF
RURAL VOTERS.
HOW DO YOU PLAN TO IMPROVE RURAL
KMUNLTS AND THE DISCUSSION ON
CLIMATE CHANGE?
>> THAT IS REALLY A GREAT
QUESTION, THANKS.
SO IT'S EARTH DAY AND FOR TOO
LONG WE HAVE BEEN DEBATING
WHETHER CLIMATE CHANGE IS
HAPPENING.
MY FAVORITE MOMENT OF THIS WHEN
JOHN OLIVER FINALLY DECIDED TO
PUT 100 SCIENTISTS ON HIS STAGE
IN WHITE COATS.
99 OF THEM WERE ON ONE ONE SIDE
AND ONE ON THE OTHER, TO SHOW
THAT THE SCIENTIFIC COMMUNITY
SAYS IT'S HAPPENING.
AND I THINK WHAT'S IMPORTANT AS
YOU LOOK AT THE GOALS IN THE
GREEN NEW DEAL AND NO ONE THINKS
WE'RE GOING TO DOT EVERY "I" AND
CROSS EVERY "T" IN A SHORT
PERIOD OF TIME, BUT WE NEED
THOSE GOALS.
WE NEED THE ENERGY OF YOUNG
PEOPLE AND PEOPLE THAT REALLY
WANT TO MOVE ON CLIMATE CHANGE.
SO THIS IS WHAT I SAY TO MY
RURAL VOTERS.
I SAY LOOK AT WHAT'S IN FRONT OF
YOU.
BECAUSE FOR TOO LONG WE'VE BEEN
TALKING ABOUT IT ON MORE OF A
COASTAL ISSUE, WHICH IS TRUE.
RISING SEA LEVELS, THE GREENLAND
SHEET ISSUE WAS IN THE NEWS
TODAY, HURRICANES.
BUT LET'S TALK ABOUT THE MIDDLE
OF THE COUNTRY WHERE WE NEED TO
POLITICAL SUPPORT.
AND I PERSONALLY THINK SOMEONE
FROM THE HEARTLAND COULD DO A
GOOD JOB OF THAT.
WHAT DO WE SEE IN FRONT OF US?
FLOODS ALL OVER IOWA, NEBRASKA,
AND MISSOURI.
THIS IS IMPORTANT SO I'M GOING
TO FINISH THIS.
WE HAVE GOT -- I FEEL YOU
CREEPING OVER MY SHOULDER, NOT
IN A TRUMPIAN MANNER.
JUST LIKE YOU'RE THERE AND
LIKE -- THIS IS, LIKE, REALLY,
REALLY IMPORTANT.
SO THIS WOMAN IN IOWA, FRAN, SHE
IS LITERALLY STANDING WITH ME
WITH BINOCULARS ON LOOKING AT
HER HOUSE WHICH IS SUBMERGED
UNDER WATER AND SHE SAYS TO ME
THIS IS WHERE I LIVE WITH MY
HUSBAND AND MY TWO 4-YEAR-OLDS,
AND I SAID IS THE RIVER RIGHT
THERE?
SHE SAYS, NO, THE RIVER IS 2 1/2
MILES AWAY.
OURS IS A HOUSE THAT'S OVER A
CENTURY OLD.
THERE'S STILL HORSEHAIR IN THE
PLASTERS, BUT THIS TIME FOR THE
FIRST TIME THE WATER CAME INTO
MY HOUSE.
THAT'S CLIMATE CHANGE.
OR YOU LOOK AT THE WILDFIRES IN
COLORADO OR ARIZONA OR YOU THINK
THAT DAD IN NORTHERN CALIFORNIA
OUTSIDE OF PARADISE WHO'S
DRIVING HIS LITTLE GIRL IN THE
CAR WITH THEIR HOUSE PRESUMABLY
BURNING BEHIND THEM, AND THE
FLAMES ARE LAPPING OVER THEIR
CAR AND HE'S SINGING TO HER,
SINGING TO HER TO CALM HER DOWN.
CLIMATE CHANGE ISN'T HAPPENING
100 YEARS FROM NOW.
IT'S HAPPENING RIGHT NOW, AND
THAT'S WHY AS YOUR PRESIDENT ON
DAY ONE I WOULD GET US BACK INTO
THE INTERNATIONAL CLIMATE CHANGE
AGREEMENT.
ALL RIGHT?
THAT'S DAY ONE.
ON DAY TWO AND DAY THREE I WOULD
BRING BACK THE CLEAN POWER RULES
THAT THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
WORKED OUT THAT WILL MAKE A BIG
DENT IN THIS.
I WILL BRING BACK THE GAS MYELIN
STANDARDS THAT THEY JUST LEFT
AND SAID, OH, SORRY, I KNOW YOU
CAR COMPANIES WERE READY TO DO
IT, BUT GUESS WHAT, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO.
THAT'S WHAT THEY DID.
AND I WOULD PROPOSE SWEEPING
LEGISLATIONS FOR GREEN BUILDINGS
AND NEW IDEAS AND WE NEED TO DO
THIS.
BECAUSE GUESS WHAT, IT'S YOU
GUYS, NOT ME.
IT'S MY DAUGHTER AND YOU GUYS
THAT ARE GOING TO BE INHERITING
THIS EARTH AND THAT'S WHY WE
NEED YOU ON THE FRONT LINE, ALL
RIGHT?
>> OUR NEXT QUESTION IS ACTUALLY
ONE I'VE NEVER HEARD BEFORE IN
ONE OF THESE TOWN HALLS.
>> OH, THAT REALLY BODES WELL
FOR ME.
I THINK I'LL SIT DOWN.
>> IF IT WERE COMING FROM A
REPORTER YOU GOT TO WORRY.
A YOUNG MAN NAMED ZACK SMITH
STUDYING POLITICS FROM
MASSACHUSETTS.
WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION?
>> GOOD EVENING, SENATOR.
MY QUESTION IS WHAT IS ONE ASAST
PECT OF YOUR LIFE AS A
POLITICIAN YOU WISH THE PUBLIC
BETTER UNDERSTOOD?
>> OKAY, THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
SO MY LIFE AS A POLITICIAN.
I THINK THAT I WISH PEOPLE
BETTER UNDERSTOOD WHY I HAVE
MADE SUCH A PRIORITY AND WHY I
CARE SO MUCH ABOUT PEOPLE WHO
GET IN TROUBLE WITH DRUGS AND
PEOPLE WHO GET IN TROUBLE WITH
DRINKING AND HOW I BELIEVE THAT
THERE ARE GRAYS IN THIS WORLD
AND THAT NOT EVERYTHING IS AN
EXTREME, THAT PEOPLE CAN MESS UP
AND GO ONTO DO GREAT THINGS AND
THAT'S WHERE THAT BELIEF COMES
FROM.
SO IN MY CASE WHEN I WAS GROWING
UP MY DAD HAD A BIG DRINKING
PROBLEM.
HE IS -- I LOVE MY DAD SO MUCH.
I JUST SAW HIM ABOUT A WEEK OR
SO AGO.
HE IS A DISTINGUISHED
JOURNALIST.
HE'S NOW RETIRED.
HE IS 91 YEARS OLD.
BUT AND IN HIS WORDS HE CAN'T
GET A LOT OF DRINKS IN THE
ASSISTED LIVING FACILITY.
BUT THE POINT IS HIS AA GROUPS
STILL VISIT HIM BECAUSE THAT'S
HOW IN HIS OWN WORDS WAS
PURSUED.
PACK THEN 20 YEARS LATER THE
LAWS HAD CHANGED AND FORCED HIM
TO GO INTO TREATMENT, AND I WAS
THERE WITH HIM WITH HIS
MINISTER, AND WITH HIS LAWYER
AND I TALKED ABOUT HOW IT HAD
HURT MY LIFE AND MY SISTER'S
LIFE, HOW WE WOULD WAIT FOR HIM
TO COME HOME ALL THE TIME, HOW
WE WOULD VANISH SOMETIMES AND BE
GONE, AND WHAT IT MEANT TO BE
GROWING UP WITH THAT.
SO WHAT I SAW IN MY LIFE IS
BECAUSE HE GOT TREATMENT AND
BECAUSE ACTUALLY THE GOVERNMENT
PUSHED HIM INTO TREATMENT IT
CHANGED HIS LIFE.
HE ENDED UP STAYING MARRIED FOR
THE THIRD TIME, BUT HE DID.
HE ENDED UP REALLY BEING ABLE TO
SPEND TIME WITH ME AND MY SISTER
LIKE HE HAD NEVER DONE BEFORE,
AND I WANT OTHER PEOPLE TO HAVE
THAT SAME RIGHT, WHETHER THEY
GET HOOK ON OPIOIDS, YOU'VE GOT
NEW HAMPSHIRE ONE OF THE BIGGEST
OPIOID EPIDEMICS ACROSS IT
COUNTRY.
WHETHER IT MEANS THEY GOT HOOKED
ON METH, NO MATTER WHAT IT IS
THAT PEOPLE HAVE THE RIGHT TO
HAVE THAT TREATMENT.
AND IN THE CASE OF OPIOIDS, BY
THE WAY, YOU KNOW WHO I'D HAVE
PAY FOR THAT TREATMENT?
THE PHARMACEUTICAL COMPANIES
THAT GOT PEOPLE HOOKED ON THE
DRUGS TO BEGIN WITH.
SO IF YOU ASKED TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT MOTIVATES ME SOMETIMES AND
WHY I CAN BELIEVE IN TOUGH LOVE
AND WHY I BELIEVE YOU HAVE TO
SET EXPECTATIONS AND STANDARDS
FOR YOURSELF AND THE PEOPLE
AROUND YOU AND WHY I BELIEVE
THAT EVERYONE HAS THAT SAME
RIGHT TO HAVE THAT LIFE THAT MY
DAD EVENTUALLY HAD IS BECAUSE OF
MY OWN LIFE EXPERIENCE, AND I
THINK IT'S SO IMPORTANT AS YOU
GUYS THINK ABOUT IF YOU WANT TO
GO INTO PUBLIC SERVICE TO HAVE
PEOPLE COME FROM ALL KINDS OF
DIFFERENT BACKGROUNDS.
WE HAVE IN THE SENATE PEOPLE
THAT GREW UP PRETTY RICH AND
PEOPLE LIKE ME WHO'S GRANDPA HAD
TO QUIT SCHOOL AND A DAD WHO
STRUGGLED WITH ALCOHOLISM AND A
MOM WHO WAS A TEACHER WHO TAUGHT
SCHOOL UNTIL SHE WAS 70 YEARS
OLD.
SHE TAUGHT SECOND GRADE BECAUSE
SHE DIDN'T HAVE ENOUGH MONEY
BECAUSE MY PARENTS GOT DIVORCED.
THAT'S MY LIFE.
AND SOMEHOW I ENDED UP BEING
ELECTED AS THE FIRST WOMAN
SENATOR IN THE STATE OF
MINNESOTA AND A C FOR
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES OF AMERICA.
OKAY, THAT IS WHAT THIS COUNTRY
IS ABOUT, ALL RIGHT?
>> LET'S TAKE A QUICK BREAK.
WE'RE GOING TO BE BACK WITH MORE
QUESTIONS FROM MINNESOTA SENATOR
AMY KLOBUCHAR RIGHT AFTER THIS.
She's staying in a rainforest
tree house? That's my dream.
You dream big for a man on a
plane to Omaha.
And she's zip lining with Little
Jon?
WHAT!
It's Lil Jon.
Even he knows that.
Thanks, Captain Obvious.
You're with Big Jon.
I'm Steve.
Don't hate-like their trip,
book yours with Hotels.com
and get rewarded basically
everywhere.
Hotels.com.
BE THERE.
DO THAT.
GET REWARDED.
PNC Bank has technology to
help make banking easier,
like...
a business borrowing solution
to help get a little more space
with a lot less mom.
or Home Insight,
to search for a new house
within your budget.
Because, they really need
their space.
PNC — make today the day.
At Panera, our salads are
uniquely crafted.
With peak season berries,
creamy avocado.
And a dressing fit
for a Goddess.
Come taste what a
salad should be.
And with Panera catering,
there's more to go around.
Panera. Food as it should be.
♪♪
They can't live without it
protection.
Detergent alone doesn't kill
bacteria,
but adding Lysol Laundry
Sanitizer kills 99.9%
with 0% bleach.
Because the things they love
can get pretty gross.
Lysol. What it takes to
protect.™
>>> WELCOME BACK TO CNN'S
SPECIAL DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
TOWN HALL EVENT.
FIRST UP TONIGHT IS SENATOR AMY
KLOBUCHAR.
WE'VE COVERED A WIDE RANGE OF
ISSUES, NOT THIS ONE THAT WE'RE
TAKING ON YET.
IT IS A VETERAN SPECIFIC ISSUE
AND A VERY IMPORTANT ONE.
WE SHOULD BRING IN TIMOTHY
BISHOP.
A GRADUATE STUDENT AND FORMER
ARMY OFFICER WHO SERVED FOR
SEVEN YEARS INCLUDING TWO
MISSIONS IN AFGHANISTAN.
SO, FIRST, SAM, THANK YOU FOR
YOUR SERVICE.
WHAT'S YOUR QUESTION?
>> SENATOR KLOBUCHAR, THANK YOU
FOR BEING HERE TONIGHT.
>> THANK YOU.
AND THANK YOU FOR YOUR SERVICE.
>> NO WORRIES.
>> I LOVE HOW YOU DOWN-PLAY IT,
BUT IT'S NOT.
>> DESPITE NEARLY 15 YEARS OF
EFFORTS VETERANS STILL COMMIT
SUICIDE ABOUT 1 1/2 TIMES THE
RATE OF AVERAGE AMERICANS.
THAT'S AFFECTED A LOT OF PEOPLE
I'VE SERVED WITH.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO AS PRESIDENT
TO TRY TO STEM THIS EPIDEMIC?
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
AND TO PLEA THIS IS AN
UNBELIEVABLE THING GOING ON.
AND WE SAW IT COMING OUT OF THE
IRAQ WAR, AFGHANISTAN, AND
RECENTLY AS YOU KNOW THEY'VE
EVEN COMMITTED SUICIDE AT
VETERANS FACILITIES, IN THE
PARKING LOT.
SO WHAT I WOULD DO IS MAKE SURE
WE HAVE THE RESOURCES TO HELP
THEM WHEN IT COMES TO MENTAL
HEALTH.
BEING SICK PHYSICALLY SHOULD BE
TREATED THE SAME AS BEING SICK
MENTALLY, ALL RIGHT?
AND THAT MEANS -- THAT MEANS
HAVING THE TYPE OF PSYCHIATRISTS
AND PSYCHOLOGISTS AND COUNSELORS
THAT WE NEED.
THAT MEANS THINGS LIKE THE
BROADER SUBJECT FOR ALL PEOPLE,
IT IS THE MENTAL HEALTH PARODY
BILL THAT MY FORMER SENATOR FROM
MINNESOTA WHO WE SADLY LOST IN A
PLANE CRASH WORKED SO HARD ON.
AND THAT SIMPLY SAYS INSURANCE
COMPANIES HAVE GOT TO HANDLE
MENTAL HEALTH THINGS JUST LIKE
THEY HANDLE PHYSICAL HEALTH
THINGS.
WHEN IT COMES TO THE VETERANS A
LOT OF THEM AS YOU KNOW GO HOME
TO SMALL TOWNS ACROSS AMERICA.
SOMETIMES THEY DON'T HAVE THE
KIND OF ACCESS ESPECIALLY IF
THEY'RE IN THE RESERVE.
SO THEY'RE ECONOMIC BACK
SPORADICALLY TO OUR VA
FACILITIES.
SO WE HAVE TO DO A LOT BETTER
JOB WHEN THEY'RE COMING BACK TO
EVALUATE THEM, SEE WHAT THEY
NEED,O TOUCH BASE WITH THEM.
IF THEY DON'T HAVE A FACILITY
NEAR THEM TO MAKE SURE THEY CAN
SEE DOCTORS AND COUNSELORS TO
HELP THEM.
THIS IS A SCOURGE ON OUR
COMMUNITIES BECAUSE WHEN THESE
VETS SIGNED UP TO SERVE THERE
WASN'T A WAITING LINE.
AND THEY COME BACK TO AMERICA
AND THEY NEED A JOB OR EDUCATION
OR HEALTH CARE INCLUDING MENTAL
HEALTH CARE, THERE SHOULD NEVER
BE A WAITING LINE IN THE UNITED
STATES OF AMERICA.
>>> NEXT QUESTION COMES FROM
OLIVIA FERDINAND.
SHE'S A SOPHOMORE FROM
CONNECTICUT.
>> HI, SENATOR.
>> HI, OLIVIA.
>> ONE OF YOUR MAIN POLICY
PROPOSALS IS A $1 TRILLION
INVESTMENT IN INFRASTRUCTURE.
INFRASTRUCTURE IS NOT AS FLASHY
AS OTHER POLICIES.
>> I'LL TRY TO MAKE IT FLASHY.
SEWER LINES?
WATER SYSTEMS.
IF YOU LIVE IN FLINT, IT'S A
PRETTY IMPORTANT THING, BUT KEEP
GOING.
ALL RIGHT?
>> DEFINITELY.
SO HOW DO YOU MAKE
INFRASTRUCTURE AN APPEALING
ISSUE FOR YOUNG VOTERS?
>> SURE.
I WAS ACTUALLY RECENTLY IN
NASHVILLE AND WE WERE TALKING
ABOUT THIS AT FISK WITH SOME OF
THE STUDENTS THERE, AND FOR A
LOT OF STUDENTS AND YOUNG
PEOPLE, THEY DON'T HAVE CARS,
LIKE MY DAUGHTER.
SO THEY CARE ABOUT TRANSIT
WHETHER YOU'RE IN A BIG CITY OR
A MEDIUM-SIZED CITY AND YOU WANT
TO GET TO WHERE YOU ARE.
MANCHESTER, ACTU THIS A
HAS ONE OF THE HIGHEST
PERCENTAGE OF PEOPLE IN THE
COUNTRY, IF NOT THE HIGHEST,
THAT DOESN'T EVEN HAVE ACCESS TO
ANY KIND OF COMMUTER RAIL YET
THEY NEED WORKERS TO COME UP TO
WORK IN THEIR JOBS.
SO I THINK YOU NEED TO TALK
ABOUT NOT JUST ROADS AND
BRIDGES, VERY IMPORTANT.
I HAD THAT BRIDGE FALL DOWN JUST
A MILE FROM MY HOUSE IN THE
MIDDLE OF A SUMMER DAY.
YES, THAT KIND OF INFRASTRUCTURE
MATTERS, BUT IT'S ALSO ABOUT
TRANSIT, IT'S ALSO ABOUT
CRUMBLING SCHOOLS LITERALLY IN
BALTIMORE, THEY HAD SOME
SCHOOLS, I SEE SOME HEADS
NODDING, THAT DIDN'T HAVE HEAT
THIS LAST YEAR.
AND WE HAVE A PRESIDENT RIGHT
NOW IN THE WHITE HOUSE THAT
CLAIMED ON ELECTION NIGHT, OH, I
REMEMBER THAT NIGHT, HE CLAIMED
THAT HE WANTED TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT INFRASTRUCTURE AND ALL
HE'S DONE IS PUT A PACKAGE
FORWARD THAT WAS ABOUT $200
BILLION AND I SHOWED HOW WE CAN
PAY FOR THIS, INCLUDING WITH THE
INFRASTRUCTURE FINANCING
AUTHORITY, BONDS, OF COURSE
DIRECT FEDERAL INVESTMENT BY
REPEALING THOSE PORTIONS OF THE
TAX CODE THAT BY THE WAY THE NEW
REPUBLIC BILL, ANY OF
YOU GUYS HAVE MOWN IN THE
BAHAMAS?
THEN YOU'RE OKAY.
BECAUSE THEY GOT $150 BILLION
OFF OF PEOPLE TO HELP WEALTHY
PEOPLE JUST BY DOING THE CHANGES
THEY MADE THERE.
SO THERE'S A WAY TO PAY FOR THIS
AND WE HAVE TO MOVE ON IT AND IT
CAN'T JUST BE RHETORIC.
YOU GUYS ONCE AGAIN WHEN IT
COMES TO INFRASTRUCTURE, IF YOU
DON'T HAVE SUBWAYS AT WORK OR
BUSES THAT GET YOU TO PLACES
WHERE YOU ARE AND YOU DON'T WANT
TO GET A CAR OR YOU CAN'T AFFORD
A CAR OR YOU HAVE A CAR AND YOU
ONLY WANT TO BRING IT CERTAIN
PLACES, INFRASTRUCTURE MATTERS
TO YOU.
DID I DO MY JOB?
OKAY.
GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS.
OKAY.
HE TOLD ME ONCE WHEN I WAS ON
HIS SHOW HE SAID GENERATIONS OF
CUOMO HAVE LOST BY RUNNING ON
INFRASTRUCTURE.
THAT'S NOT REALLY TRUE.
THEY WON AS GOVERNOR OF NEW
YORK, BUT CONTINUE ON.
>> BETTER THAN CREEPING AFTER
YOU.
>> SO FAR AWAY NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
>> SO LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS AS A
LARGER ISSUE.
LET'S BRING IN SARAH TROPIANO.
SHE'S A JUNIOR AT SAT. ANSELM
COL
COLLEGE.
IMPORTANT CULTURAL QUESTION.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE?
>> HI, SENATOR.
YOU ARE A KEY FIGURE IN THE
JUDGE KAVANAUGH HEARING AND MANY
FEMALE VOTERS FORMED A STRONG
OPINION ON YOUR POLITICS.
IF YOU HAD ONE THING TO SAY TO
YOUNG FEMALE VOTERS OR COLLEGE
STUDENTS, WHAT WOULD IT BE AND
WHY?
>> WELL, I WOULD SAY THAT PLEASE
RUN FOR OFFICE.
RIGHT NOW I THINK WE HAVE
SOMETHING LIKE -- WE'RE NOW UP
TO OVER 25 WOMEN IN THE SENATE.
THAT'S GOOD BECAUSE IN THE
HISTORY OF THE SENATE WE'VE HAD
OVER 2,000 MEN AND SOMETHING
LIKE 50 WOMEN.
I WAS ON TREVOR NOAH'S SHOW HE
SAID IF A NIGHTCLUB HAD A RATIO
LIKE THAT THEY WOULD SHUT IT
DOWN, OKAY?
SO I WOULD SUGGEST THAT YOU RUN
FOR OFFICE.
THAT YOU GET INVOLVED IN
CAMPAIGNS.
BY THE WAY, IT DOESN'T HAVE TO
BE A PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN,
ALTHOUGH I'D LOVE TO HAVE YOU
SIGN UP FOR MINE AND YOU CAN
TEXT AMY AT 91990 OR YOU CAN GO
TO OUR WEB
WEBSITE @AMYKLOBUCHAR.COM.
I DID THAT, TEAM, THANK YOU.
SO WE WOULD LOVE TO HAVE YOU
INVOLVED IN OUR CAMPAIGN AND I'M
SURE MY FRIENDS WHO ARE RUNNING
AS WELL WOULD LIKE THAT.
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO RUN YOURSELF.
YOU CAN GET INVOLVED IN
NONPROFITS.
ONE OF THE THINGS WE LEARNED
FROM THE KAVANAUGH HEARING, WE
HAVE ADDED SOME GREAT WOMEN TO
THE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE.
BUT FOR SO LONG, UNTIL ABOUT TWO
YEARS AGO, IT WAS JUST TWO OF
US.
TWO WOMEN AND LIKE 22 MEN.
THOSE ARE THE RATIOS THAT WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
AND THAT MOMENT, BY THE WAY, WAS
ANOTHER MOMENT FOR ME WHERE I
WAS JUST TRYING TO DO MY JOB AND
ASK HIM QUESTIONS AND YOU KNOW
THAT WAS AN ISSUE OF DR.
CHRISTINE BLASS SEE FORD AND HER
COURAGEOUS TESTIMONY.
WHEN I WAS TRYING TO SINK UP
WHAT HE SAID AND WHAT SHE SAID,
IF YOU REMEMBER HE WENT AFTER
ME, HE SAID, HAVE YOU EVER
BLACKED OUT?
I SAID, YOU KNOW WHAT, I WANT
YOU TO ANSWER THE QUESTION.
I WANT YOU TO ANSWER THE
QUESTION.
WHEN YOU HAVE ALCOHOLISM IN YOUR
FAMILY, YOU DON'T MESS AROUND
WITH STUFF LIKE THAT.
AND HE ENDED UP COMING BACK AND
APOLOGIZING TO ME, BUT I THINK
YOU SAW AT THAT MOMENT IF ANY OF
YOU WATCHED THAT THAT YOU CAN BE
STRONG AND FIRM BUT YOU DON'T
HAVE TO GO DOWN AND ACT LIKE HE
DID TO BE IN PUBLIC SERVICE IN
THIS COUNTRY.
>> QUICKLY BEFORE WE SAY
GOOD-BYE.
ON THAT NOTE, WHAT IS ONE THING
THAT YOU HOPE YOUR DAUGHTER HAS
IN HER LIFETIME THAT YOU DIDN'T
HAVE IN YOURS?
>> OH, WELL I HOPE THAT SHE CAN
GO THROUGH HER LIFE WITHOUT
PEOPLE ASKING YOU THINGS LIKE
CAN A WOMAN ACTUALLY BEAT DONALD
TRUMP?
ANSWER, YES.
I HOPE THAT SHE CAN GO THROUGH
HER LIFE, AN ISSUE WE HAVEN'T
TALKED ABOUT, WITHOUT HAVING
THAT FEAR OF GUNS IN THE HANDS
OF PEOPLE THAT SHOULDN'T HAVE
THEM AND THAT IS SOMETHING THAT
I PLEDGE TO YOU AS YOUR
PRESIDENT, AND THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT SHOULD MATTER TO YOUR
GENERATION, I WILL TAKE ON IN A
BIG WAY.
IT IS A CRIME THAT WE DON'T HAVE
UNIVERSAL BACKGROUND CHECKS AND
THAT WE HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING TO
FURTHER THAT ISSUE.
AND I'LL END WITH THIS BECAUSE
YOU GUYS, THIS IS YOUR MOMENT.
WHEN I LOOK AT THE ARC OF THE
LAST YEAR AND WHAT WE'VE BEEN
THROUGH THE LAST TWO YEARS, YOU
START THE DAY AFTER DONALD TRUMP
GOT SWORN IN WHERE WOMEN AND MEN
PEACEFULLY MARCHED ALL OVER THIS
COUNTRY.
YOU GO TO DAY TEN WHEN HE PUT
OUT THAT HORRIBLE ANTI-MUSLIM
ORDER.
THE ANTI-REFUGEE ORDER WHERE
PEOPLE SPONTANEOUSLY SHOWED UP
AT THE AIRPORTS INCLUDING A
BUNCH OF YOUNG PEOPLE.
DAY 100, MY FAVORITE MARCH, THE
MARCH FOR SCIENCE.
WHAT DO WE WANT, SCIENCE?
WHEN DO WE WANT IT?
AFTER PEER REVIEW.
YOU GO THROUGH THE FALL ON THIS
INCREDIBLE VICTORY FOR DIGNITY
AND RACISM.
DOUG JONES GOT ELECTED IN THE
STATE OF ALABAMA AND THEN YOU GO
TO DAY 429 WHEN THOSE PARKLAND
YOU STUDENTS CAPTURED THE
ATTENTION OF THE WORLD.
THEY SPOKE OUT.
THAT IS YOUR GENERATION AND THEN
WE TOOK OVER THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES.
WHY?
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T JUST TALK TO
EACH OTHER, YOU VOTED AND YOU
DIDN'T JUST VOTE, YOU TALKED TO
YOUR PARENTS AND YOUR
GRANDPARENTS.
I'VE BEEN WORKING ON THAT ISSUE
A LONG TIME.
THE MOMS IN SANDY HOOK TRIED
THEIR BEST AND COULDN'T GET IT
DONE.
WHEN I WAS IN LAW ENFORCEMENT WE
TRIED TO GET IT DONE AND IF WE
GET BESTED BY A BUNCH OF 19 AND
20-YEAR-OLDS, THAT'S THE BEST
THING I EVER HEARD.
SO VOTE AND GET INVOLVED.
>> SENATOR AMY KLOBUCHAR.
GOOD LUCK GOING FORWARD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> NEXT UP, SENATOR ELIZABETH
WARREN.
STAY WITH CNN.
I switched to MiraLAX
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives
forcefully stimulate
the nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX works with
the water in your
body to unblock your
system naturally.
And it doesn't cause
bloating,
cramping, gas,
or sudden urgency.
MiraLAX.
Look for the pink cap.
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it
from your allergy pills?
Flonase relieves
your worst symptoms
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
Flonase helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances.
Most pills only block one.
Flonase.
At Fidelity, we help you
prepare for the unexpected
with retirement planning and
advice for what you need today
and tomorrow.
Because when you're
with Fidelity,
there's nothing to stop you
from moving forward.
-Keep it down there.
I have a system.
-Keith used to be great
to road-trip with.
But since he bought his house...
Are you going 45?
-Uh, yes.
55 is a suggestion.
-...it's kind of like driving
with his dad.
-What a sign, huh?
Terry, can you take
a selfie of me?
-Take a selfie of you?
-Yeah.
Can you make it look
like I'm holding it?
-He did show us how to bundle
home and auto at progressive.com
and save a bunch of money.
-Oh, a plaque.
"He later navigated northward,
leaving...
Progressive can't protect you
from becoming your parents.
But we can protect
your home and auto
when you bundle with us.
HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN  HIGU
LIVE? WELL YOU CAN, WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITE INTERNET WHEREVER YOU