ABOUT 95% OF STUDENTS WHO HAVE
DEBT.
>> I SUPPORT ANYTHING THAT IS
ABOUT REDUCING THE DEBT OF
STUDENT LOANS.
>> I HAVE FOUGHT HARD WITH SOME
SUCCESS TO MOVE TOWARD MAKING
PUBLIC COLLEGES AND UNIVERSITIES
TUITION-FREE.
>> I WISH I COULD STAPLE A FREE
COLLEGE DI UNDER■■■■■■■■■■■■ O
OF YOUR CHAIRS.
I DO.
DON'T LOOK.
IT'S NOT THERE.
>> OH, I'M SORRY, I WAS JUST
LOOKING TO SEE IF A FREE COLLEGE
DIPLOMA WAS UNDER MY CHAIR.
I WAS HOPING.
WHAT YOU SEE THERE IS THE
DIFFERENCE.
ELIZABETH WARREN SAYING LOOK,
WE'RE GOING TO FIND WAYS NOT
JUST TO MAKE PUBLIC COLLEGES
FREE.
WE'RE ALSO GOING TO WORK ON
DEBT.
THEN YOU SAY HARRIS AND SANDERS
SAY THAT'S A GOOD IDEA, WOULD
LIKE TO HEAR MORE ABOUT IT.
KLOBUCHAR, THE REALIST, THE
PRAGMATIST GROUND, SAYING I
WOULD LOVE TO DO THIS FOR YOU
BUT I CAN'T.
>> SO WE SEE ALL OF THAT.
ANOTHER THING THAT CAME UP, WE
WERE EXPECTING EDUCATION BECAUSE
SENATOR WARREN RELEASED THAT
PLAN YESTERDAY IN THE MORNING.
THIS, I DON'T THINK ANYONE SAW
COMING.
TALKING ABOUT VOTING RIGHTS FOR
FELONS.
AND THIS IS STILL GETTING A LOT
OF ATTENTION.
THIS IS NOT THE LAST WE WILL
HEAR OF IT.
>> IT WILL CONTINUE TO GET A LOT
OF ATTENTION.
IT STARTED WITH WHAT BERNIE
SANDERS SAID, LET'S PLAY THAT
AND THEN SOME OF THE REACTION TO
IT.
GO AHEAD.
>> I THINK THE RIGHT TO VOTE IS
INHERENT TO OUR DEMOCRACY.
YES, EVEN FOR TERRIBLE PEOPLE.
BUT I DO BELIEVE THAT EVEN IF
THEY ARE IN JAIL, THEY'RE PAYING
THEIR PRICE TO SOCIETY, BUT THAT
SHOULD NOT TAKE AWAY THEIR
INHERENT AMERICAN RIGHT TO
PARTICIPATE IN OUR DEMOCRACY.
>> SHOULD PEOPLE CONVICTED OF
SEXUAL ASSAULT, OF THE BOSTON
MARATHON BOMBER, SHOULD THEY BE
ABLE TO VOTE?
>> WHILE INCARCERATED?
>> YES.
>> NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
>> I AGREE THAT THE RIGHT TO
VOTE IS ONE OF THE VERY
IMPORTANT COMPONENTS OF
CITIZENSHIP, AND IT'S SOMETHING
THAT PEOPLE SHOULD NOT BE
STRIPPED OF NEEDLESSLY.
>> SO A LOT OF KAMALA HARRIS'
ANSWERS, AS YOU HEARD, WITH THE
EXCEPTION OF ON GUNS, A LOT OF
HER ANSWERS WERE LIKE, I'M
INTERESTED IN TALKING MORE ABOUT
THAT, WHICH IS SORT OF SHE
DOESN'T WANT TO TAKE A POSITION.
PETE BUTTIGIEG CLEARLY SAYING
NO, I DON'T THINK THAT FELONS
WHO ARE CURRENTLY INCARCERATED
SHOULD BE VOTING.
BERNIE SANDERS, LOOK, GIVE THE
GUY THIS.
THIS IS NOT A POLITICALLY SAVVY
POINT TO TAKE, WHICH IS TO SAY
YEAH, THE BOSTON BOMBER SHOULD
BE ABLE TO VOTE.
I MEAN, THAT'S NOT SOMETHING
THAT A POLITICAL CONSULTANT
WOULD TELL YOU TO SAY.
WELL, IN CERTAIN CASES WE NEED
TO MAKE EXCEPTIONS, ET CETERA.
SANDERS EVEN ACKNOWLEDGED THAT
IN THE TOWN HALL WHERE HE SAID
I'M PROBABLY WRITING A 30-SECOND
AD FOR MY OPPONENTS.
HE'S DEFINITELY WRITING AN AD TO
YOUR POINT THIS ISN'T GOING AWAY
ANY TIME SOON.
>> YOU POINTED OUT KAMALA
HARRIS.
SHE NEEDED TO STUDY A LOT OF
THINGS LAST NIGHT, BUT NOT, AS
YOU POINT OUT, WHEN IT COMES TO
GUN CONTROL, TO GUN SAFETY
LEGISLATION.
>> SHE WAS CLEARLY READY ON THIS
ONE.
OBVIOUSLY, KNOWING WHAT THE 20th
ANNIVERSARY OF COLUMBINE
PASSING, SHE WOULD GET THESE
QUESTIONS.
LET'S GO TO WHAT SHE SAID.
>> WE NEED REASONABLE GUN SAFETY
LAWS IN THIS COUNTRY STARTING
WITH UNIVERSAL BACKGROUND CHECKS
AND A RENEWAL OF THE ASSAULT
WEAPON BAN.
BUT THEY HAVE FAILED TO HAVE THE
COURAGE TO ACT.
UPON BEING ELECTED, I WILL GIVE
THE UNITED STATES CONGRESS 100
DAYS TO GET THEIR ACT TOGETHER
AND HAVE THE COURAGE TO PASS
REASONABLE GUN SAFETY LAWS.
IF THEY FAIL TO DO IT, I WILL
TAKE EXECUTIVE ACTION.
>> RIGHT.
SO IF YOU DIDN'T WATCH THE TOWN
HALL, THAT IS IN DIRECT CONTRAST
TO A LOT OF HER ANSWERS WHICH
WERE MUCH MORE FUZZY.
SHE CLEARLY WANTS TO STAND OUT
ON THAT ISSUE.
WE DO KNOW, IF YOU ASK
DEMOCRATIC VOTERS, THEY WANT
MORE GUN CONTROL.
THAT INCLUDES REINSTATEMENT OF
THE ASSAULT WEAPONS BAN.
OBVIOUSLY, IT HASN'T HAPPENED IN
CONGRESS.
I WONDER IF THEY VOTE ON IT.
THAT'S ALWAYS BEEN THE ISSUE.
HOW MUCH SALIENCE DOES IT HAVE
AS A VOTING ISSUE.
KAMALA HARRIS BETTING IT HAS A
BUNCH, PARTICULARLY WITH
PARKLAND, WITH THE 20th
ANNIVERSARY OF COLUMBINE.
AN INTERESTING PLACE, SHE'S
TAKING A STAND AND A HARD STAND
THERE WHILE BEING RELATIVELY
FUZZY ABOUT A LOT OF THE OTHER
ISSUES WE RAN THROUGH.
>> CHRIS CILLIZZA, ALWAYS A
PLEASURE.
>> JOINING ME NOW, CNN POLITICAL
COMMENTATOR MIA LOVE.
FORMER REPUBLICAN REPRESENTATIVE
FROM UTAH, AND JOE TRIPPI, A
DEMOCRATIC STRATEGIST.
JOE, AS WE LOOK AT BOAT OF THIS,
I WANT TO PICK UP WHERE WE LEFT
OFF WITH CHRIS CILLIZZA.
IN TERMS OF KAMALA HARRIS COMING
DOWN STRONG AND SAYING LISTEN, I
WILL IN FACT ISSUE AN EXECUTIVE
ORDER IF THAT'S WHAT IT WILL
TAKE TO GET THIS DONE.
TALKING ABOUT GUNS.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT BERNIE
SANDERS WRITING AN OPO AD FOR
REPUBLICANS.
IS THIS ONE ALSO, JOE?
>> WE DON'T KNOW YET.
YOU'RE SEEING CANDIDATES TAKE
STRONG POSITIONS WHERE THEY WANT
TO AND TRY TO LEAD THE PARTY IN
THEIR DIRECTION.
THAT OFTEN WORKS.
IT OFTEN DOESN'T.
I WAS WITH HOWARD DEAN IN 2004.
I WAS HIS CAMPAIGN MANAGER.
WE LED ON OPPOSING THE WAR ON
CIVIL UNIONS FOR GAY COUPLES,
WHICH WAS VERY CONTROVERSIAL.
WE LED.
WE STARTED RAISING MORE MONEY
THAN ANYBODY.
WE TOOK A LEAD IN THE POLLS.
BUT IN THE END, THE PARTY TURNED
TO JOHN KERRY, SOMEBODY THEY
THOUGHT WAS SAFER, WHO WAS FOR
THE WAR, AGAINST ALL THE THINGS
THAT HAD CREATED OUR CANDIDACY
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
SO WHEN YOU SEE KAMALA HARRIS,
WHEN YOU SEE ELIZABETH WARREN
LEADING ON STUDENT LOAN DEBT AND
ON FREE COLLEGE TUITION AND
THESE KINDS OF THINGS, IT
DOESN'T NECESSARILY MEAN THAT
THE PARTY IS GOING TO GO THERE.
IT'S DEFINITELY SALIENT.
IT'S DEFINITELY GOT A LOT OF
ENERGY.
WE'LL SEE WHERE IT GOES FROM
HERE.
YOU SAW MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIEG
IMMEDIATELY SLAP DOWN WHERE
BERNIE SANDERS WAS GOING ON
GIVING FELONS THE RIGHT TO VOTE
WHILE THEY WERE IN PRISON, SO
WE'LL SEE THESE FIGHTS CONTINUE,
BUT YOU'RE SEEING A VERY DIVERSE
FIELD ACTUALLY COME UP WITH A
LOT OF DIVERSE IDEAS, AND SOME
OF THEM WILL EMERGE.
SOME WILL BE DUDS, BUT WE'LL
SEE.
>> IN TERMS OF IDEAS THAT ARE
EMERGING, OBVIOUSLY, A LOT OF
THE CONVERSATION DRIVEN BY THE
PROPOSAL WE SAW FROM SENATOR
WARREN RELEASED YESTERDAY IN THE
MORNING.
CONGRESSWOMAN, I'M WONDERING, AS
WE LOOK AT THAT, WHILE IT MAY
NOT BE A PLAN REPUBLICANS WANT
TO GET BEHIND, THERE IS A REAL
DESIRE IN THIS COUNTRY FOR A
FRANK DISCUSSION ABOUT THE
SOARING STUDENT DEBT, HOW IT IS
CRIPPLING YOUNG PEOPLE IN THIS
COUNTRY, AND WHAT CAN BE DONE
ABOUT IT.
WILL THIS PUSH REPUBLICANS TO
TALK ABOUT THEIR SOLUTIONS?
>> NOW, HERE'S A PLACE WHERE I
THINK THEY CAN ACTUALLY GET SOME
SORT OF FOOTING, ESPECIALLY WITH
PEOPLE WHO ARE REPUBLICANS WHO
DON'T NECESSARILY LIKE THE
PRESIDENT BUT THEY'RE TRYING TO
GET SOME OF THOSE VOTES.
THE PROBLEM IS, IT'S IN THE HOW.
PEOPLE WANT TO SEE HOW YOU'RE
GOING TO BE ABLE TO GET MORE
STUDENTS AWAY FROM THIS
CRIPPLING STUDENT LOAN DEBT.
I WOULD SAY THE BEST THING YOU
COULD DO IS FIND A WAY TO LOWER
THE COST OF HIGHER EDUCATION.
THEREBY GIVING AS MANY PEOPLE AS
MUCH ACCESS TO HIGHER EDUCATION
AS
>>> IF YOU'RE SAYING I'M JUST
GOING TO MAKE IT FREE, THE NEXT
QUESTION IS SHOW ME THE PLAN ON
HOW TO PAY FOR IT BECAUSE I'LL
TELL YOU RIGHT NOW WHAT'S NOT
WORKING IS IMPOSING A 70% TAX TO
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO WORK.
YOU'VE GOT TO FIGURE OUT HOW ARE
YOU GOING TO PAY THOSE
INSTITUTIONS TO MAKE SURE THAT
THEY CAN ACTUALLY GIVE
EDUCATION, AND BY THE WAY, HOW
ARE YOU GOING TO HOLD THESE
INSTITUTIONS ACCOUNTABLE FOR THE
MONEY THAT THEY ARE GETTING, THE
UNLIMITED FLOW OF FEDERAL
DOLLARS THAT THEY ARE GETTING,
TO ENSURE THAT THESE STUDENTS
ARE GRADUATING IN AN AREA WHERE
THEY CAN ACTUALLY WORK AND THEY
ARE NOT COMPLETELY INDEBTED WITH
STUDENT LOANS?
THOSE ARE THE TYPES OF
CONVERSATIONS THAT I THINK WILL
ACTUALLY STICK WITH PEOPLE THAT
ARE LOOKING FOR SOMEWHERE ELSE
TO VOTE.
>> AS WE LOOK -- GO AHEAD,
SORRY, JOE, WERE YOU GOING TO
SAY ANYTHING?
>> ALL THESE CONVERSATIONS ARE
GOING TO HAPPEN IN THE
DEMOCRATIC RACE FOR PRESIDENT
RIGHT NOW AND IN THE HOUSE ON
THE DEMOCRATIC SIDE.
DEBATE WITHIN THE PARTY.
THERE IS ABSOLUTELY NO -- ALMOST
NO DEBATE ON ANY OF THESE THINGS
WITHIN THE REPUBLICAN PARTY
WHATSOEVER, NOT IN THE
PRESIDENTIAL RACE, NOT IN THE
SENATE, NOT IN THE HOUSE.
IT IS JUST --
>> THAT'S.
>> THERE ARE NO ANSWERS.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> WELL, IT IS TRUE.
>> IT'S NOT.
>> MOST PEOPLE CAN SEE THAT,
THAT YOU'RE NOT SEEING THE KIND
OF DEBATE.
>> I'VE TALKED ABOUT THIS MORE
YEARS AS A MEMBER OF CONGRESS.
I TALKED ABOUT IT ALL THE TIME.
>> I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE NOT IN THE HOUSE ANYMORE.
I'M TALKING ABOUT WITHIN THEIR
CAMPAIGNS THERE'S ALMOST NO
DEBATE ABOUT MANY OF THESE
ISSUES AND THE WAY THAT YOU ARE
SEEING THE DIVERSE DEBATE ON THE
DEMOCRATIC SIDE WHICH IS A GREAT
CONVERSATION FOR THE COUNTRY TO
BE SEEING.
I'M NOT MAKING A HIT ON THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY, BUT THE BIG
SPIRITED DEBATE SEEMS TO BE
HAPPENING ON THE DEMOCRATIC
SIDE.
>> THAT'S BECAUSE YOU'VE GOT A
LOT OF PEOPLE THAT ARE TRYING TO
SET THEIR PLACE IN THE DEMOCRAT
PARTY.
THEY ARE TRYING TO DIFFERENTIATE
THEMSELVES FROM SOMEBODY ELSE.
RIGHT NOW YOU ONLY HAVE ONE
REPUBLICAN NOMINEE OR WHOEVER IS
PRESUMED THE NOMINEE WHICH IS
THE PRESIDENT, SO --
>> THE TRUMP PARTY.
>> THE REASON THE DEBATES ARE
HAPPENING IS BECAUSE YOU HAVE SO
MANY DIFFERENT DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES OUT
THERE, AND THEY ARE TRYING TO
SET A SPOT FOR THEMSELVES, A
PLACE FOR THEMSELVES SO THEY CAN
DIFFERENTIATE THEMSELVES FROM
SOMEBODY ELSE.
>> WELL, THEY ARE CERTAINLY
GIVING US A LOT TO TALK ABOUT,
AND THE GOOD NEWS IS WE CAN HEAR
FROM ALL KINDS OF PEOPLE ON THIS
PROGRAM, AND WE'LL DO MUCH MORE
OF IT IN THE COMING DAYS AND
MONTHS.
THANK YOU BOTH FOR BEING WITH
US.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> COMING UP, A CRITICAL
QUESTION, OR IS IT ACTUALLY A
VEILED ATTEMPT TO FIND
<,4■ ■■÷■■■■÷■÷■■■■■÷÷■■■÷■■■■4
CITIZEN QUESTION TO THE 2020
CENSUS.
WE'RE LIVE OUTSIDE THE COURT
NEXT.
Lease the 2019 RX 350 for
$409 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■
Metastatic breast
cancer is relentless,
but I was relentless first.
Relentless about learning the
first song we ever danced to.
About teaching him
to put others first.
About helping her
raise her first child.
And when I was first diagnosed,
my choice was everyday Verzenio.
It's the only one of its kind
that can be taken every day.
It gives us more time
without cancer progressing.
Verzenio is the only
CDK4 & 6 inhibitor
approved with hormonal therapy
that can be taken every day
for postmenopausal women
with HR+, HER2- MBC.
Diarrhea is common,
may be severe,
or cause dehydration
or infection.
Before taking Verzenio,
tell your doctor
if you have fever, chills,
or other signs of infection.
Verzenio may cause low
white blood cell counts,
which may cause
serious infection
that can lead to death.
Serious liver
problems can occur.
Symptoms include tiredness,
appetite loss, stomach pain,
and bleeding or bruising.
Blood clots that can lead
to death have occurred.
Tell your doctor if you
have pain or swelling
in your arms or legs,
shortness of breath, chest pain,
rapid breathing or heart rate,
or if you are pregnant,
nursing, or plan to be pregnant.
Common side effects
include nausea, infections,
low blood cells and platelets,
decreased appetite, headache,
abdominal pain,
tiredness, vomiting,
and hair thinning or loss.
My relentless reason: it's them.
My choice with my
doctor: it's Verzenio.
Ask your doctor if
everyday Verzenio
is right for your
first treatment.
Ok everyone!
Our mission is to
provide complete,
balanced nutrition
for strength and energy!
Whoo-hoo!
Great-tasting Ensure.
With nine grams of protein
and twenty-six vitamins
and minerals.
Ensure, for strength
and energy.
and twenty-six vitamins
and minerals.
♪ ♪
Hey Alleddlers...■
ACHOO!
...do yoheads?
Try ZYRTEC...pá
...it starts hard at
■ay.    hour oAnd HH
ZYRTEC Muddle No More.
Don't tell your mother.
Dad, it's fine.
We have ALLSTATE.
AND WITH CLAIMRATEGUARD
THEY WON'T RAISE YOUR RATES
JUST BECAUSE OF A CLAIM.
That's why you're my favorite...
I KNOW.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
>>> TODAY SUPREME COURT JUSTICES
ARE HEARING ONE OF THE MOST
IMPORTANT CASES OF THIS TERM.
AT ISSUE, WHETHER EVERY PERSON
IN THE UNITED STATES SHOULD BE
ASKED ABOUT THEIR CITIZENSHIP
STATUS FOR THE 2020 CENSUS.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION SAYS
THE QUESTION WILL STRENGTHEN
FEDERAL VOTING RIGHTS LAWS, BUT
CRITICS SAY IT COULD ACTUALLY
INTIMIDATE NON-CITIZENS AND ALSO
HISPANICS AND AFFECT RESPONSE
RATES.
LET'S CHECK IN OUTSIDE THE
SUPREME COURT.
WHAT ARE PEOPLE SAYING?
>> Reporter: WITH THIS DEEPLY
DIVIDED SUPREME COURT REALLY
WRESTLED WITH THE QUESTION OF
WHETHER OR NOT THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION CAN ADD■ ■■,■■■■
LIKE■■CATIV■■■
END OF THE ARGUMENT SEEMED L■
WERE GOING TO■■■■■■■■■■■ W THE
JUSTICES"■■■■■!!!! ■ GOR AND
CHIEF JUSTICE JOHN ROBERTS ■@DN
POINT HE DID HAVE A QUESTION
THAT WAS SYMPATHETIC TO THE VER
WHO SOMETIMES HEAD FAKES DURING
NOTED, LOOK, OTHERNTRIES
HAVE SIMILAR QUESTIONS HERE, AND
HE SAID THAT THE SECRETARYB ■■■N
IN THIS AREA, AAAúE,
ERICA, THIS■■ION HAS NOT
BEEN ASKED OF ALL RECIPIENTS
SINCE 1950, AND THE DATA THAT
COMES OUT OF THE CENSUS IS
CRITICAL.
IT GOES TO THE ALLEGATION OF
SEATS IN THE CONGRESS AS WELL AS
BILLIONS OF DOLLARS OF FEDERAL
FUNDS, AND THESE HALF DOZEN
STATES CAME TO COURT TO ARGUE
THAT THIS WAS GOING TO HURT
TURNOUT FOR MINORITIES AND IT
WAS GOING TO INTIMIDATE THEM
FROM COMING FORWARD, BUT THE
GOVERNMENT SAID, LOOK, WE THINK
THAT THIS WAS IMPORTANT TO
COMPLY WITH THE VOTING RIGHTS
ACT.
ONE MORE THING, ERIKA, IT'S
IMPORTANT TO KNOW THAT THREE
LITTLE COURT JUDGES HAVE RULED
AGAINST THE ADMINISTRATION HERE,
PARTICULARLY LOOKING AT THE
JUSTIFICATION, BECAUSE SECRETARY
ROSS SAID, LOOK, THE DEPARTMENT
OF JUSTICE IN 2018 ASKED ME TO
ADD THIS TONNN■ON, BUT INFACT T
TRIAL IT'S REVEALED THAT ALL THE
WAY BACK IN 2017 ROSS WORKED
WITH OTHER HARDLINERS WITH THE
ADMINISTRATION TRYING TO FIND A
WAY TO GET THIS QUESTION IN SO
THIS IS GOING TO BE A BIG TEST
FOR THIS NEWLY SOLIDIFIED
CONSERVATIVE MAJORITY HERE ON
THE SUPREME COURT.
>> ALL EYES.
THANK YOU.
AND THANKS TO ALL OF YOU FOR
JOINING ME TODAY.
SITTING IN FOR KATE BALDUAN.
"INSIDE POLITICS" WITH JOHN KING
STARTS RIGHT NOW.■2■2■2■2■2■2■22
>> WELCOME TO "INSIDE POLITICS."
I'M JOHN KING.
THANK YOU FOR SHARING YOUR DAY
WITH US.
THE SUPREME COURT HEARING
ARGUMENTS TODAY IN A BIG