HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN  HIGU
LIVE? WELL YOU CAN, WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITE INTERNET WHEREVER YO.
YOU'LL GET 25MBPS, PLUS BUILT-IN
WI-FI, AND THERE'S NO HARD DATA
LIMITS. SO, WHEREVER YOU LIVE,
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
EVERYTHING YOU LOVE ONLINE.
CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, STAY
INFORMED, WATCH THE LATEST
VAHEAD. NO WONDER HUGHESNET I■R
SATELLITE INTERNET. ACT NOW TO
SAVE BIG WITH OUR LIMITED TIME
OFFER. GET FREE STANDARD
INSTALLATION BY CALLING RIGHT
NOW. SO, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING
FOR? GET HUGHESNET GEN5. TO
ORDER, CALL THE NUMBER ON YOUR
SCREEN. BE SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR
HOME PHONE SERVICE, TOO. CALL
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN
TODAY.
7>> WELCOME
SPECIAL NIGHT AT ST. ANSELM
COLLEGE IN MANCHESTER, NEW
HAMPSHIRE.
I'M ANDERSON COOPER.
WE ARE JUST GETTING STARTED WITH
OUR CNN PRESIDENTIAL TOWN HALL
EVENT.
IN THE LAST HOUR YOU HEARD FROM
SENATOR AMY KLOBUCHAR.
LATER TONIGHT YOU'LL SEE CORY
SANDERS, KAMALA HARRIS AND PETE
BUTTIGIEG.
TO PULL THIS EVENT OFF CNN HAS
PARTNERED WITH HARVARD
UNIVERSITY'S COLLEGE OF
POLITICS.
ALSO WITH THE NEW HAMPSHIRE
INSTITUTE OF POLITICS RIGHT HERE
AT ST. ANSELM COLLEGE.
THROUGHOUT THE NIGHT THE
CANDIDATES WILL TAKE QUESTIONS
FROM THESE YOUNG COLLEGE
STUDENTS AND YOUNG ADULTS WHO
ARE IN THE AUDITORIUM WHO SAY
THEY PLAN TO VOTE IN THEIR
STATE'S DEMOCRATIC PRIMARIES AND
CAUCUSES.
WELCOME TO THE STAGE PLEASE,
SENATOR ELIZABETH WARREN.
>> HI.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
HI.
>> HAVE A SEAT?
>> ARE WE GOING TO DO STUDENTS?
>> LET'S GO RIGHT TO IT.
>> IN THAT CASE, I WANT CLOSER.
HAVE TO KEEP AN EYE ON THE ONES
IN THE BACK.
>> I WANT TO START WITH YOUR BIG
ANNOUNCEMENT TODAY ABOUT COLLEGE
AFFORDABILITY.
IT COULD IMPACT A LOT OF
STUDENTS HERE.
I WANT TO BRING IN DENA MILLER
FROM MASSACHUSETTS.
SHY'S A JUNIOR STUDYING HISTORY.
DENA.
>> HI, SENATOR.
I LIKE SO MANY OTHER STUDENTS
HAD TO TAKE OUT LOANS TO PAY FOR
MY EDUCATION THAT I WILL BE
PAYING FOR YEARS.
WHAT IS YOUR PLAN FOR STUDENT
DEBT?
>> THANKS FOR THE QUESTION,
DENA.
THIS IS THE AMERICA WE LIVE IN
NOW.
BASICALLY TO GET A SHOT AT A
MIDDLE CLASS LIFE YOU'VE GOT TO
HAVE SOME POST HIGH SCHOOL
TECHNICAL TRAINING, TWO-YEAR
COLLEGE, FOUR-YEAR COLLEGE,
MAYBE GRADUATE SCHOOL DEPENDING
ON WHO YOU ARE AND WHAT YOU'RE
ENDING UP DOING.
THE POSITION OF THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT HAS BEEN, GOOD LUCK
TO YOU, YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
THE ONE THING THEY'VE DONE,
THETHEY
H
HAVE' DONE IS LENT TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS TO
STUDENTS.
IT IS CRUSHING THEM.
MY PROPOSAL IS TO SAY, THIS
ISN'T RIGHT.
WHAT WE HAVE TO DO AS A COUNTRY
IS ROLL BACK THAT DEBT.
SO I HAVE TWO PARTS TO THE
PROPOSAL.
PART ONE IS THAT WE SAY THAT
WE'RE GOING TO ROLL BACK STUDENT
LOAN DEBT FOR ABOUT 95% OF
STUDENTS WHO HAVE DEBT.
THAT'S PART ONE.
AND PART TWO IS TO MAKE SURE
THAT WE NEVER GET IN THIS MESS
AGAIN ON STUDENT LOAN DEBT AND
THAT IS TO MAKE COLLEGE
UNIVERSALLY AVAILABLE WITH FREE
TUITION AND FEES AND TO PUT MORE
MONEY INTO PELL GRANTS SO THAT
STUDENTS OF COLOR, SO THAT OUR
POOREST STUDENTS HAVE REAL
ACCESS TO COLLEGE AND THAT WE
PUT REAL MONEY INTO OUR
UNIVERSITIES.BLACK COLLEGES AND
THIS IS ABOUT OPPORTUNITY FOR
EVERYONE.
AND CAN WE TALK ABOUT HOW TO PAY
FOR IT?
>> I WAS JUST ABOUT TO ASK FOR
IT.
>> THAT IS THE CRITICISM FOR
REPUBLICANS, HOW TO PAY FOR IT.
CENTRIST DEMOCRATS SAY DOESN'T
THIS FEED THE NARRATIVE THAT
DEMOCRATS WANT TO GIVE
EVERYTHING AWAY FOR FREE.
>> LET'S REMEMBER WHERE THIS ALL
STARTED.
I STARTED SEVERAL MONTHS AGO
ABOUT A WEALTH TAX.
IT'S 2 CENTS ON EVERY DOLLAR
ABOVE THE GREAT FORTUNES ABOVE
50 MILLION DOLLARS.
SO YOUR 50 MILLIONTH AND FIRST
DOLLAR YOU HAVE TO PAY TWO CENTS
ON ALL OF THE DOLLARS AFTER
THAT.
HERE'S THE STUNNING PART.
IF WE ASK THE GREAT FORTUNES IN
THIS COUNTRY, UNDERSTAND, THIS
ISN'T ABOUT TRYING TO BE NASTY
OR SAY YOU'VE DONE ANYTHING
WRONG, WHAT IT'S ABOUT IS
SAYING, LOOK, YOU HAD A GREAT
IDEA.
YOU GOT OUT THERE.
YOU WORKED HARD OR YOU INHERITED
WELL.
WHICHEVER ONE IT WAS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> BUT NOW THAT YOU'VE GOT THAT
GREAT FORTUNE, SPEND JUST A
MINUTE TO REMEMBER HOW YOU GOT
IT.
YOU BUILT THAT GREAT BUSINESS OR
YOUR ANCESTORS DID USING WORKERS
THAT ALL OF US HELPED PAY TO
EDUCATE.
YOU GOT YOUR GOODS TO MARKET
USING ROADS AND BRIDGES THAT ALL
OF US HELPED PAY TO BUILD.
YOU ARE PROTECTED IN YOUR
FACTORIES WITH FIREFIGHTERS AND
POLICE OFFICERS THAT ALL OF US
HELPED TO PAY.
AND WE SAY, GOOD FOR YOU, THAT
YOU HAVE NOW GOTTEN THIS GREAT
FORTUNE, BUT TWO CENTS.
YOU'VE GOT TO PAY SOMETHING BACK
SO EVERYBODY ELSE GETS A CHANCE.
AND HERE'S HOW THE MONEY WORKS
OUT.
IF WE PUT THAT TWO CENT WEALTH
TAX IN PLACE ON THE 75,000
LARGEST FORTUNES IN THIS
COUNTRY, TWO CENTS, WE CAN DO
UNIVERSAL CHILD CARE FOR EVERY
BABY ZERO TO 5, UNIVERSAL PRE-K,
UNIVERSAL COLLEGE AND KNOCK BACK
THE STUDENT LOAN DEBT BURDEN FOR
95% OF OUR STUDENTS AND STILL
HAVE NEARLY A TRILLION DOLLARS
LEFT OVER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> YEAH.
>> I WANT YOU TO -- THI1&■■ ■ ■M
MICK FROM PENNSYLVANIA.
>> HI, MEGHAN.
>> SHE'S A GRADUATE STUDENT AT
HARVARD AND M.I.T.
SHE'S A CONTRIBUTOR AT FORBES.
YOU MAKE ME FEEL LIKE A SCHLUB.
I MEAN --
>> WHAT DO YOU DO IN YOUR SPARE
TIME, MEGHAN?
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
SO AMAZON'S MONOPOLY MEANS I CAN
BUY GENERIC GOODS AND BRANDS
FROM MY PHONE AND RECEIVE THEM
ON MY DOORSTEP WITHOUT A
DELIVERY FEE WITHIN 24 HOURS.
HOW IS BREAKING UP BIG TECH GOOD
FOR ME?
>> OKAY.
GOOD QUESTION, MEGHAN.
HERE'S WHAT WE WANT TO REMEMBER
ABOUT AMAZON, ABOUT GOOGLE,
ABOUT APPLE, ABOUT A LOT OF
THESE GIANT TECH COMPANIES.
THEY ACTUALLY RUN TWO
BUSINESSES.
SO ONE IS THE PLATFORM.
THAT'S THE PLACE WHERE PEOPLE
COME TO BUY AND SELL GOODS.
THAT'S WHERE YOU GO TO GET
WHATEVER IT IS, YOU KNOW, YOU
CAN COMPARE 48 PRINTERS AND GET
IT ALL DELIVERED IN LESS THAN 24
HOURS.
GOT IT.
COOL.
THAT'S THE PLATFORM.
JUST SO YOU GET AN IDEA OF THE
SCALE HERE FOR AMAZON, WALMART
DOES ABOUT 9% OF ALL RETAIL
SALES IN AMERICA.
IF YOU WANT TO SELL ONLINE,
AMAZON IS DOING ABOUT 49% OF ALL
RETAIL SALES THAT ARE HAPPENING
IN AMERICA.
SO THAT IS THE MARKETPLACE.
SO AMAZON RUNS THE MARKETPLACE.
I'M COOL WITH THAT.
I'M ALL FOR A MARKETPLACE, BUT
AMAZON DOES A SECOND THING AND
THAT IS THEY COLLECT INFORMATION
ON EVERY BUYER AND SELLER WHO
COMES THROUGH.
EVERY TIME YOU GO TO BUY
SOMETHING, THEY GET YOUR
INFORMATION AND THEY AGGREGATE
IT WITH THE OTHER INFORMATION
THEY HAD ABOUT YOU.
EVERY TIME YOU COME TO SELL
SOMETHING THEY GET INFORMATION.
AND THEN THEY SEE THAT, WHOA,
OVER THERE IT LOOKS LIKE PET
PILLOWS IS STARTING TO MAKE A
BIG PROFIT.
HUH, SAYS AMAZON.
I KNOW WHAT WE'LL DO.
LET'S JUMP IN FRONT OF PET
PILLOWS AND DO AMAZON PET
PILLOWS AND MOVE PET PILLOWS
FROM THE FRONT PAGE BACK TO PAGE
16 AND THE CONSEQUENCE IS THAT
AMAZON, BECAUSE OF ITS SUPERIOR
INFORMATION, CAN COME IN AND
KNOCK OUT ALL OF THE
COMPETITION.
NOW THIS IS A REAL THING,
MEGHAN, THAT'S HAPPENING.
HERE'S WHAT WE KNOW AS A
CONSEQUENCE OF THIS, IS THAT THE
AREA AROUND THESE GIANTS ARE
REFERRED TO BY VENTURE
CAPITALISTS, INVESTORS, AS THE
DEAD ZONE BECAUSE IT MEANS YOU
TRY TO START UP A BUSINESS, YOU
JUST RUN THE RISK THAT AMAZON
STEPS IN FRONT OF YOU OR GOOGLE
STEPS IN FRONT OF YOU OR THEY
BUY YOU OUT BEFORE YOU HAVE A
CHANCE TO GET STARTED.
LOOK, HERE'S HOW I SEE IT.
YOU CAN RUN THE PLATFORM, THAT
IS, YOU CAN BE THE UMPIRE IN THE
BASEBALL GAME AND YOU CAN RUN AN
HONEST PLATFORM, OR YOU CAN BE A
PLAYER, THAT IS, YOU CAN HAVE A
BUSINESS OR YOU CAN HAVE A TEAM
IN THE GAME, BUT YOU DON'T GET
TO BE THE UMPIRE AND HAVE A TEAM
IN THE GAME.
IF WE BREAK OFF THE PLATFORM
FROM THE PARTS THAT ARE
COMPETING, WHAT YOU'LL SEE IN
AMERICA IS A PLATFORM THAT WORKS
REALLY WELL.
IT'S A VERY PROFITABLE BUSINESS
BUT YOU'LL SEE A LOT MORE
COMPETITION WHERE LITTLE
BUSINESSES HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
GOING WHERE WHEN YOU'VE GOT A
GOOD IDEA YOU CAN BUILD THAT
GOOD IDEA INTO SOMETHING, WHERE
THERE'S REALLY A CHANCE FOR
EVERYBODY TO GET IN AND COMPETE.
SO THAT'S THE REASON I WANT TO
SEE THE TWO OF THEM BROKEN
APART.
>> DO YOU ORDER STUFF FROM
AMAZON?
>> SURE.
>> YOU DO?
WHAT WAS THE LAST THING YOU
ORDERED, DO YOU KNOW?
>> A MAILBOX.
>> OKAY.
WHAT DID THEY PUT THE MAILBOX IN
WHEN THEY DELIVER IT?
>> IT COMES IN A BOX.
IT WAS A BOX OF MAILBOX.
>> WE HAVE ANOTHER QUESTION NOW.
>> OKAY.
>> THIS IS SETH PHILO FROM
ARIZONA.
HE'S A SUPPORTER OF BUTTIGIEG.
>> IN 2012 YOU OPPOSED THE SALE
OF MARIJUANA YET IN 2016 YOU
CAME OUT IN SUPPORT OF THE
LEGALIZATION OF MARIJUANA
NATIONWIDE.
WHAT ARE YOUR HONEST VIEWS ON
THE LEGALIZATION OF MARIJUANA
AND MARIJUANA LEGISLATION AND IF
THEY HAVE, WHY HAVE THEY
CHANGED?
>> SO, ACTUALLY, I SUPPORTED
MASSACHUSETTS CHANGING ITS LAWS
ON MARIJUANA.
MASSACHUSETTS HAD DECRIMINALIZED
AT THAT POINT AND I THOUGHT IT
MADE A LOT MORE SENSE FOR
MASSACHUSETTS TO GO AHEAD AND
LEGALIZE MARIJUANA, AND I NOW
SUPPORT THE LEGALIZATION OF
MARIJUANA.
AND LET ME TELL YOU AT LEAST A
COUPLE OF REASONS WHY.
THE FIRST ONE IS, IT'S JUST A
PLAIN OLD SCIENCE REASON.
IT MAKES NO DARN SENSE THAT
RIGHT NOW IN AMERICA WE TREAT
MARIJUANA AS A SCHEDULE 1 DRUG,
WHICH MEANS IN EFFECT THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT HAS
DETERMINED IN ADVANCE THAT IT
HAS NO MEDICINAL USE, THAT IT
CAN'T HAVE ANY GOOD EFFECTS, NO
RESEARCH IS SUPPOSED TO BE DONE.
IT MAKES IT VERY HARD TO DO
RESEARCH ON IT AND THAT'S
JUST -- WE SHOULD BE DOING THIS,
RIGHT?
WE SHOULD BE LOOKING INTO IT.
BUT THE SECOND REASON IS BECAUSE
OF THE RACIAL IMPACT OF THE
ENFORCEMENT OF MARIJUANA LAWS.
YOU KNOW, RIGHT NOW IN THIS
COUNTRY THE BEST EVIDENCE
SUGGESTS THAT AFRICAN-AMERICANS
AND WHITES USE MARIJUANA AT
ABOUT THE SAME RATES AND YET
AFRICAN-AMERICANS ARE FAR MORE
LIKELY TO BE ARRESTED FOR
MARIJUANA USE THAN WHITES ARE.
SO EVERY TIME WE START TO TALK
ABOUT CRIMINAL JUSTICE REFORM,
FOR EXAMPLE, I THINK A GOOD
PLACE TO START IS WITH THE
THINGS WE MAKE ILLEGAL, AND ONE
OF THE BEST PLACES WE COULD
START IS BY LEGALIZING
MARIJUANA.
>> I WANT YOU TO MEET JACKSON
DWYER, HE'S FROM MASSACHUSETTS.
HE'S A SENIOR AT ST. ANSELM
COLLEGE.
>> HI, JACKSON.
>> HI, SENATOR.
>> YOU HAVE OFTEN BEEN A VOCAL
CRITIC OF STATE POLICERS.
HOW CAN YOU ASSURE ME THAT YOU
WILL SUPPORT LEGISLATION THAT
KEEPS LAW ENFORCEMENT SAFE?
>> SO THAT'S A VERY GOOD
QUESTION.
I APPRECIATE YOUR ASKING IT.
YOU KNOW, I TALK WITH A LOT OF
PEOPLE IN DIFFERENT PARTS OF THE
CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM, PEOPLE
WHO ARE LAW ENFORCEMENT, PEOPLE
WHO ARE IN THE JUDICIAL SYSTEM,
PEOPLE WHO ARE IN -- PEOPLE WHO
ARE INCARCERATED, VARIOUS PARTS
OF IT, AND WHAT ALL OF THEM TELL
ME IS WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM.
OUR CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM IS
BROKEN, AND RIGHT AT THE HEART
OF THAT PROBLEM IS RACE.
AND WE HAVE TO ADDRESS THIS HEAD
ON.
SO LET ME JUST GIVE YOU SOME
BASIC INFORMATION ABOUT WHAT'S
HAPPENING RIGHT NOW IN OUR
CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM.
STUDY AFTER STUDY AFTER STUDY
SHOWS US THAT AFRICAN-AMERICANS
COMPARED WITH WHITES ARE MORE
LIKELY TO BE FOR EXACTLY THE
SAME CRIMES, THEY'RE MORE LIKELY
TO BE ARRESTED, THEY'RE MORE
LIKELY TO BE ARRAIGNED, THEY ARE
MORE LIKELY TO BE TAKEN TO
TRIAL.
THEY ARE MORE LIKELY TO BE
WRONGFULLY CONVICTED AND THEY
ARE MORE LIKELY TO RECEIVE
HARSHER SENTENCES.
THIS IS A CRIMINAL JUSTICE
SYSTEM THAT IS NOT ONLY LOCKING
UP TOO MANY PEOPLE, IT IS A
CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM THAT HAS
A PROBLEM OF RACE RIGHT AT THE
HEART OF IT, AND WE NEED TO CALL
IT OUT FOR WHAT IT IS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> NO ONE IS SAFER IN A WORLD
WHERE WE HAVE A BROKEN CRIMINAL
JUSTICE SYSTEM, SO LET ME JUST
GO THROUGH A COUPLE OF THE PARTS
DIRECTLY TO YOUR QUESTION.
I SAID ON THE FIRST PART ONE WAY
WE CAN HELP FIX THIS SYSTEM IS
TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT IT IS WE
MAKE IT ILLEGAL.
HOW ABOUT THE NEXT PART IN THE
JUDICIAL SYSTEM?
WE NEED TO MAKE SURE THAT
EVERYBODY IS ENTITLED AND GETS
GOOD LEGAL REPRESENTATION.
THROUGHOUT THE SYSTEM WE WANT TO
MAKE SURE THE RIGHT PEOPLE ARE
INCARCERATED AND NOT THE WRONG
PEOPLE BECAUSE THEY COULDN'T
AFFORD TO HIRE A LAWYER.
JUSTICE IS NOT JUST FOR THOSE
WHO ARE RICH, JUSTICE IS FOR
EVERYONE AND THE ONLY WAY WE'RE
ABLE TO GET THAT IN AMERICA IS
IF WE'RE ABLE TO PUT THE
RESOURCES INTO IT.
THIRD PART OFHIS I■ROFIT PRIVAT
PRISONS.
IT IS AN OUTRAGE IN AMERICA.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> SFFOURTH IS THAT WHEN PEOPLE
LEAVE THE PRISON SYSTEM, THEY
NEED TO BE REINTEGRATED.
THEY NEED TO BE ABLE TO FIND A
JOB, FIND DECENT HOUSING,, AND
THEY NEED TO BE ABLE TO
PARTICIPATE IN THE POLITICAL
PROCESS.
AND THAT MEANS THEY NEED THE
RIGHT TO VOTE TO BE REINSTATED.
THEY ARE AMERICAN CITIZENS.
ONE MORE, YOU TALK ABOUT SAFETY
FOR OUR POLICE OFFICERS AND YOU
ARE RIGHT.
THIS IS A VERY SERIOUS ISSUE.
ONE OF THE MAIN WAYS THAT WE
COULD HELP MAKE OUR POLICE SAFER
IS TO GET SERIOUS ABOUT GUN
SAFETY IN THIS COUNTRY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
.
YOU MENTIONED SARGEANT GANNON'S
TRAGIC DEATH IN MASSACHUSETTS.
I WROTE AN OP ED WITH HIS
PARENTS ABOUT ASKING FOR OUR
LEADERS ACROSS THIS COUNTRY TO
STEP UP AND PASS SOME SENSIBLE
GUN SAFETY LAWS.
WE NEED UNIVERSAL BACKGROUND
CHECKS, WE NEED TO TAKE WEAPONS
OF WAR OFF OUR CITY STREETS.
RIGHT NOW WE LIVE IN AMERICA
WHERE 7 CHILDREN AND TEENAGERS
WILL DIE EVERY SINGLE DAY, WHERE
THE LIVES OF OFFICERS ARE PUT AT
RISK.
WE NEED AS A COUNTRY TO STEP UP,
TO BE MORE RESPONSIBLE, TO BE
WILLING TO PUSH BACK AGAINST THE
NRA AND TO PUT SOME SENSIBLE GUN
SAFETY LAWS IN PLACE.
I THINK THAT WILL BE THE BEST
THAT WE CAN DO.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR QUESTION.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THIS IS ELLIE TAYLOR.
SHE'S FROM WISCONSIN.
SHE'S A STUDENT AT HARVARD AND A
FRESHMAN.
>> HI, ELLIE.
>> HI, SENATOR.
THIS ISN'T AS MUCH OF A
POLICY-BASED QUESTION.
SOME PEOPLE HAVE VOICED YOU
GETTING HILLARIED IN THE
ELECTION SO WHAT LESSONS HAVE
YOU LEARNED FROM 2016 THAT WILL
HELP YOU TO KIND OF NAVIGATE
THESE SITUATIONS WHEN YOU MIGHT
BE CRITICIZED FOR SOMETHING
THAT'S PARTIALLY MOTIVATED BY
SEXIST.
>> THAT'S A REALLY GOOD
QUESTION, BUT IF I CAN, I WANT
TO GO BACK BEFORE 2016.
CAN WE ALL JUST LET OUR HAIR
DOWN HERE FOR A MINUTE?
THIS DIDN'T JUST START IN 2016.
BEEN AROUND FOR A WHILE.
I'LL TELL YOU WHEN I RAN INTO IT
BIG TIME.
I NEVER THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO
BE IN ELECTED POLITICS.
I'VE KNOWN WHAT I WANTED TO DO
ALL MY LIFE.
I WANTED TO BE A TEACHER.
I THOUGHT THAT WOULD BE MY JOB
FOREVER.
DURING THE CRASH I END UP DOWN
IN WASHINGTON SETTING UP A
CONSUMER AGENCY FOR PRESIDENT
OBAMA.
AFTER I DID THAT FOR A YEAR, THE
REPUBLICANS SAID, WE'RE NEVER
GOING TO LET HER STAY AND RUN
THAT THING.
I CAME BACK TO MASSACHUSETTS.
THERE WAS A VERY POPULAR
REPUBLICAN INCUMBENT.
HE HAD HIGH APPROVAL RATINGS, HE
HAD A BUCKET OF MONEY IN THE
BANK FROM WALL STREET AND HE HAD
JUST BEATEN A WOMAN WHO WAS
REALLY GOOD AND EVERYBODY
THOUGHT WAS GOING TO WIN.
SO I START GETTING THESE PHONE
CALLS FROM PEOPLE AND THEY SAY,
ELIZABETH, YOU SHOULD RUN
AGAINST HIM FOR THE SENATE SEAT.
YOU SHOULD DO IT.
GO AHEAD.
YOU SHOULD DO THIS THING.
YOU'RE GOING TO LOSE, BUT YOU
SHOULD DEFINITELY DO -- THESE
WERE DEMOCRATS CALLING ME.
SAYING, YOU SHOULD DO THIS.
YOU'RE GOING TO LOSE.
ALL I CAN SAY IS DEMOCRATS, GET
A BETTER MESSAGE.
BUT PEOPLE SAID TO ME, YOU'RE
GOING TO LOSE BECAUSE
MASSACHUSETTS IN 2011, ACCORDING
TO CONVENTIONAL WISDOM, WAS NOT
READY TO HAVE A WOMAN SENATOR OR
GOVERNOR.
WE NEVER HAD AND PEOPLE SAID
IT'S JUST NOT GOING TO HAPPEN, ■
GENERATION.
NOW YOU CAN IMAGINE HOW I HEARD
THAT.
I HEARD THAT AS, GET IN THIS
RACE, RIGHT NOW, WHICH IS WHAT I
DID.
SO I JUMPED IN THE RACE AND SURE
ENOUGH, YOU KNOW, THE EARLY
COVERAGE IS ABOUT WHAT I'M
WEARING.
IT'S ABOUT MY HAIR.
IT'S ABOUT MY VOICE.
IT'S ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT I
SMILE ENOUGH.
I DIDN'T.
IT WAS EVERY PART OF THAT.
THIS KEPT UP AND I THOUGHT, YOU
KNOW, LOOK, I'M GOING TO BE IN
THIS RACE.
I'M GOING TO MAKE SOMETHING
COUNT EVERY SINGLE DAY.
SO EVERY DAY WHEN I SAW A LITTLE
GIRL, I WOULD COME UP AND I'D
USUALLY GET DOWN, I'M A TEACHER,
AND I WOULD SAY, HI, MY NAME IS
ELIZABETH AND I'M RUNNING FOR
SENATE BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT GIRLS
DO.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> AND THEN WE WOULD PINKY SWEAR
TO REMEMBER, AND SO EVERY NIGHT
WHEN I WENT HOME, NO MATTER WHAT
THE DAY HAD BEEN LIKE, I WOULD
COUNT UP HOW MANY PINKY SWEARS
WE HAD DONE DURING THE DAY.
AND I KEPT GETTING OUT THERE AND
HAMMERING MY MESSAGE.
I KEPT GETTING OUT THERE TALKING
ABOUT WHAT'S HAPPENING WITH
WORKING FAMILIES ACROSS THE
COUNTRY, TALKING ABOUT HOW
WASHINGTON WORKS GREAT FOR THE
RICH AND THE POWERFUL, JUST NOT
WORKING FOR ANYONE ELSE, AND HOW
WE'VE GOT TO FIGHT BACK AGAINST
THAT.
SO I TALKED ABOUT IT EVERY
SINGLE DAY AND ULTIMATELY I WENT
FROM 17 POINTS BEHIND THAT GUY
TO BEATING HIM BY 7 1/2.
SO THE WAY I SEE IT IS HERE WE
ARE IN A PRESIDENTIAL, AND IT'S
THE SAME KIND OF YOU STAY AFTER
IT EVERY DAY.
ONE■ SAY YOU PERSIST.
[ SE ]
>> ORGANIZE, BUILD A GRASSROOTS
MOVEMENT, FIGHT FOR WORKING
PEOPLE, AND THAT'S HOW I'M GOING
TO BE THE FIRST WOMAN ELECTED
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A QUICK
BREAK.
WE'LL BE BACK MORE WITH THE CNN
PRESIDENTIAL TOWN HALL.
♪ ♪
Leave no man behind.
Or child.
Or other child.
Or their new friend.
Or your giant nephews
and their giant dad.
Or a horse.
Or a horse's brother,
for that matter.
The room for eight,
9,000 lb towing Ford Expedition.
Everyone's got to listen to mom.
When it comes to reducing the
sugar in your family's diet,
Coke, Dr Pepper and Pepsi hear
you.
We're working together to do
just that.
Bringing you more great tasting
beverages with less sugar
or no sugar at all.
Smaller portion sizes,
clear calorie labels and
reminders to think balance.
Because we know mom wants what's
best.
More beverage choices, smaller
portions, less sugar.
BalanceUS.org
Feel the clarity of
non-drowsy Claritin
and relief from
Symptoms caused
by over
200 indoor
and outdoor
allergens.
Like those
from buddy.
Because stuffed
animals
are clearly no substitute
for real ones.
Feel the clarity.
And Live Claritin clear.
-We bought a house
in a neighborhood
with a lot of other
young couples.
Then we noticed
something...strange.
Oh, could you, uh,
make me a burger?
-Poof -- you're a burger.
[ Laughter ]
-Everyone acts like
their parents.
-You have a tattoo.
-Yes.
-Fun. Do you not work?
-So, what kind of mower
you got, Seth?
-I don't know.
Some kid comes over.
We pay him to do it.
-But it's not all bad.
Someone even showed us
how we can save money
by bundling home and auto
with Progressive.
Progressive can't protect you
from becoming your parents.
But we can protect
your home and auto.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
WE'RE LIVE IN MANCHESTER, NEW
HAMPSHIRE, FOR A SPECIAL CNN
DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL EVENT.
FIVE TOWN HALL EVENTS TONIGHT.
ALL OF THEM TAKING QUESTIONS
FROM COLLEGE STUDENTS.
RIGHT NOW IT IS SENATOR
ELIZABETH WARREN'S TURN.
I DO WANT TO ASK YOU, YOU HAVE
CALLED FOR IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDINGS TO BE INITIATED
AGAINST PRESIDENT TRUMP.
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO THOSE
DEMOCRATS THAT SAY THIS IS NOT
THE TIME.
IT WILL TAKE AWAY THE FOCUS FROM
THE ELECTION IN 2020.
SPEAKER PELOSI SAID SHE DIDN'T
HAVE A PLAN TO DO IT.
>> THERE IS NO POLITICAL
CONVENIENCE TIME EXCEPTION TO
THE UNITED STATES CONSTITUTION.
THIS ONE IS -- IF I CAN, I WANT
TO TAKE A LITTLE TIME ON THIS
BECAUSE I THINK THIS IS REALLY
IMPORTANT.
LAST THURSDAY I HAD BEEN OUT --
I HAD BEEN TO SOUTH CAROLINA.
THIS WAS ALL ABOUT CLIMATE
CHANGE.
THAT'S WHERE I WAS, SOUTH
CAROLINA, COASTAL COMMUNITIES
PROTESTING OFF SHORE DRILLING.
I THEN CAME TO COLORADO, THE
BIGGEST DROUGHT IN 1200 YEARS.
AND THEN TO UTAH WHERE THEY HAD
ONE OF THE WORST WILDFIRE
SEASONS IN A GENERATION.
I'M ON AN AIRPLANE AND THE
MUELLER REPORT DROPS AND I START
READING IT ON THROUGH THE
EVENING, I READ IT INTO THE WEE
HOURS OF THE MORNING AND WHEN I
GET TO THE END, THREE THINGS
JUST JUMP OFF THE PAGE.
I DON'T CARE IF YOU'RE A
DEMOCRAT, REPUBLICAN,
INDEPENDENT, LIBERTARIAN,
VEGETARIAN, THREE THINGS JUST
TOTALLY JUMP OFF THE PAGE.
THE FIRST IS THAT A HOSTILE
FOREIGN GOVERNMENT ATTACKED OUR
2016 ELECTION IN ORDER TO HELP
DONALD TRUMP.
THE EVIDENCE IS JUST THERE.
READ IT, FOOTNOTE AFTER
FOOTNOTE, PAGE AFTER PAGE
DOCUMENTATION.
PART TWO, DONALD TRUMP WELCOMED
THAT HELP.
SO ON THE FIRST ONE ABOUT WHAT
THEY DID, UNDERSTAND, THIS WAS A
SOPHISTICATED ATTACK.
THEY ATTACKED PART OF VOTING
SYSTEM.
THAT'S GOING TO BE AN ONGOING
FEDERAL SYSTEM.
THEY HACKED INTO MORE THAN 50
COMPUTERS AT THE DNC, THE DCCC.
AYE VERY SERIOUS ATTACK.
AND DONALD TRUMP WELCOMING IT.
IN THE MUELLER REPORT, JUST READ
IT.
HE GETS OFF THE PHONE FROM AN
UNNAMED CALLER AND LOOKS UP AND
SAYS TO THE OTHER PERSON ON THE
PHONE, THERE ARE MORE LEAKS
COMING.
THE IDEA THAT HE WAS WELCOMING
WHAT WAS HAPPENING FROM THE
RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT, AND BY THE
SUMMER OF 2016 THE REPORT
DOCUMENTS THAT BY THAT POINT THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION -- THE
TRUMP CAMPAIGN ACTUALLY HAD A
WORKED OUT FORMAL PROCESS FOR
DEALING WITH THE LEAKS THAT WERE
COMING IN FROM THE RUSSIANS.
SO THAT'S PART TWO.
PART THREE IS WHEN THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT STARTS TO INVESTIGATE
PART ONE AND PART TWO, DONALD
TRUMP TOOK REPEATED STEPS
AGGRESSIVELY TO TRY TO HALT THE
INVESTIGATION, DERAIL THE
INVESTIGATION, PUSH THE
INVESTIGATION SOMEWHERE ELSE BUT
OTHERWISE KEEP THAT
INVESTIGATION FROM GOING FORWARD
AND TURNING INTO A SERIOUS
INVESTIGATION ABOUT A HOSTILE
FOREIGN GOVERNMENT THAT IT
ATTACKED US AND ABOUT HIS OWN
PERSONAL INTERESTS.
SO HERE'S HOW I SEE THIS.
IF ANY OTHER HUMAN BEING IN THIS
COUNTRY HAD DONE WHAT'S
DOCUMENTED IN THE MUELLER
REPORT, THEY WOULD BE ARRESTED
AND PUT IN JAIL.
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE IS A
SERIOUS CRIME IN THIS COUNTRY,
BUT MUELLER BELIEVED BECAUSE OF
THE DIRECTIONS FROM DONALD
TRUMP'S JUSTICE DEPARTMENT THAT
HE COULD NOT BRING A CRIMINAL
INDICTMENT AGAINST A SITTING
PRESIDENT.
I THINK HE'S WRONG ON THAT, BUT
THAT'S WHAT HE BELIEVED.
SO HE SERVES THE WHOLE THING UP
TO THE UNITED STATES CONGRESS
AND SAYS IN EFFECT, IF THERE'S
GOING TO BE ANY ACCOUNTABILITY,
THAT ACCOUNTABILITY HAS TO COME
FROM THE CONGRESS.
AND THE TOOL T WE ARE GIVEN
FOR THAT ACCOUNTABILITY IS THE
IMPEACHMENT PROCESS.
THIS IS NOT ABOUT POLITICS, THIS
IS ABOUT PRINCIPLE.
THIS IS ABOUT WHAT KIND OF A
DEMOCRACY WE HAVE.
IN A DICTATORSHIP EVERYTHING IN
GOVERNMENT REVOLVES AROUND
PROTECTING THE ONE PERSON AT THE
CENTER BUT NOT UNDER OUR
DEMOCRACY AND NOT UNDER OUR
CONSTITUTION.
WE HAVE CHECKS AND BALANCES, AND
WE HAVE TO PROCEED HERE IN A WAY
UNDERSTANDING OUR PLACE IN
HISTORY THAT NOT ONLY PROTECTS
DEMOCRACY NOW BUT PROTECTS
DEMOCRACY WHEN THE NEXT
PRESIDENT COMES IN AND THE NEXT
PRESIDENT AND THE PRESIDENT
AFTER THAT.
>> BUT YOU --
>> THAT'S OUR RESPONSIBILITY.
>> BUT YOU STARTED OFF BY
SAYING -- BY TALKING ABOUT SOME
OF YOUR TRAVELS AND PEOPLE
TALKING ABOUT CLIMATE CHANGE,
THEIR CONCERNS, TABLETOP ISSUES.
>> YES.
>> DOESN'T PUTTING A LOT OF
PEOPLE'S FOCUS ON IMPEACHING THE
PRESIDENT, IT WON'T GO ANYWHERE
IN THAT SENSE, DOESN'T THAT TAKE
AWAY FOCUS FROM THE TABLETOP
ISSUES THAT YOU AND OTHER
DEMOCRATS SAY YOU WANT TO RUN
ON?
>> IF YOU'VE ACTUALLY READ THE
MUELLER REPORT, IT'S ALL LAID
OUT THERE.
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S GOING TO TAKE
A LONG TIME TO FIGURE THAT OUT.
IT'S THERE.
IT'S GOT THE FOOTNOTES, IT'S GOT
THE POINTS, IT CONNECTS DIRECTLY
TO THE LAW.
BUT THIS REALLY IS
FUNDAMENTALLY -- I TOOK AN OATH
TO UPHOLD THE CONSTITUTION OF
THE UNITED STATES AND SO DID
EVERYBODY ELSE IN THE SENATE AND
IN THE HOUSE, AND I BELIEVE THAT
EVERY PERSON IN THE SENATE AND
THE HOUSE OUGHT TO HAVE TO VOTE
AND TO SAY EITHER, YEAH, THAT'S
OKAY WITH ME.
YEAH, LET A PRESIDENT JUST STEP
IN THE WAY HE DID WHEN HE TOLD
THE WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL TO GO
FIRE MUELLER, AND THEN TOLD THE
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL TO GO LIE
ABOUT HAVING TOLD THE WHITE
HOUSE COUNSEL TO GO FIRE
MUELLER, AND THEN TOLD THE WHITE
HOUSE COUNSEL TO WRITE A LETTER
SAYING THAT DONALD TRUMP HAD NOT
TOLD HIM TO GO FIRE MUELLER AND
THEN TO SAY, WHY ON EARTH WOULD
YOU TAKE NOTES ABOUT WHAT I SAID
TO YOU?
THE LAWYERS I DEAL WITH NEVER
PUT ANYTHING IN WRITING.
IF THERE ARE PEOPLE IN THE HOUSE
OR THE SENATE WHO WANT TO SAY
THAT'S WHAT A PRESIDENT CAN DO
WHEN THE PRESIDENT IS BEING
INVESTIGATED FOR HIS OWN
WRONGDOINGS OR WHEN A FOREIGN
GOVERNMENT ATTACKS OUR COUNTRY,
THEN THEY SHOULD HAVE TO TAKE
THAT VOTE AND LIVE WITH IT FOR
THE REST OF THEIR LIVES.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I WANT YOU TO MEET -- THIS IS
CECELIA DARMS.
SHE'S A SOPHOMORE AT HARVARD.
SHE INTERNT FOR HILLARY
CLINTON'S PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN.
>> HI.
>> YOU ARE REGISTERED AS A
REPUBLICAN IN 1995.
>> I WAS.
>> BUT YOU'VE SINCE BECOME ONE
OF THE MOST PROGRESSIVE PEOPLE
IN CONGRESS.
DID YOU CHANGE YOUR BELIEVES OR
DO YOU BELIEVE THE POLITICAL
PARTIES CHANGED AROUND YOU?CECE.
I GREW UP IN A FAMILY THAT
WASN'T POLITICAL.
I GREW UP OUT IN OKLAHOMA AND TO
THIS DAY I COULDN'T TELL YOU HOW
MY PARENTS WERE REGISTERED OR MY
GRANDPARENTS OR MUCH OF ANYBODY
ELSE.
MY MOM ALWAYS VOTED.
I KNOW THAT, AND IN FACT SHE
WORKED AT THE POLLS SOMETIMES,
BUT WE WEREN'T A POLITICAL
FAMILY.
AND WHEN I WAS A YOUNG MOM AND
STRUGGLING TO TRY TO KEEP UP
WITH MY JOB AND GET DINNER ON
THE TABLE AND TAKE CARE OF A
COUPLE OF LITTLE KIDS AND LAUNCH
MY CAREER, I DIDN'T THINK MUCH
ABOUT POLITICS.
NOW I'VE BEEN A POLICY PERSON
FOR A LONG, LONG TIME SO I THINK
THE QUESTION YOU'RE ASKING ME IS
WHEN DOES THE CHANGE COME?
AND THAT I CAN TELL YOU.
SO IN LATE HID 1990s I HAD BEEN
WORKING OVER AND OVER AND OVER
ON WHAT'S HAPPENING TO AMERICA'S
WORKING FAMILIES, TO AMERICA'S
MIDDLE CLASS, HOW IT IS THAT
PEOPLE WHO WORK HARD, WHO PLAY
BY THE RULES ARE JUST FINDING A
PATH STEEPER AND ROCKIER YEAR BY
YEAR AND FOR PEOPLE OF COLOR
EVEN STEEPER AND EVEN ROCKIER.
THIS IS MY LIFE'S WORK.
SO I KEEP WORKING ON THIS ABOUT
WHAT'S CHANGING IN AMERICA?
I'M STUDYING FAMILIES THAT GO
BANKRUPT, AND THE CREDIT CARD
COMPANIES, HALF DOZEN GIANT
CREDIT CARD COMPANIES FIGURE OUT
THAT IF THEY CAN GET THE
BANKRUPTCY LAWS CHANGED, THAT
WHAT WILL HAPPEN IS THEY CAN
IMPROVE THEIR BOTTOM LINE BY
JUST A LITTLE BY KEEPING PEOPLE
LOCKED OUT OF BANKRUPTCY.
NEVER MIND THAT THERE'S PEOPLE
THAT ARE HEAD OVER HEELS IN
MEDICAL DEBTS, THAT THEY'VE HAD
JOB LOSSES OR A DEATH OR
IN THE FAMILY BUT THEY'VE BEEN
CHEATED BY CREDIT CARD COMPANIES
AND MORTGAGE COMPANIES.
NEVER MIND ANY OF THAT.
I LOOKED AROUND THE MIDDLE OF
THAT FIGHT AND I REALIZED ALL
THE MONEY WAS ON ONE SIDE AND
ALL THE HURTING WAS ON THE OTHER
AND THAT'S WHEN I JUMPED IN
POLITICALLY.
I GOT IN THAT FIGHT AND I FOUGHT
IT FOR TEN YEARS, AND BY THE END
OF THAT FIGHT I FULLY UNDERSTOOD
THAT EVERY SINGLE REPUBLICAN
STOOD THERE FOR THE BANKS AND
HALF OF THE DEMOCRATS DID.
SO MY PARTY WAS THE PARTY THAT
AT LEAST WE GOT HALF OF THEM TO
STAND UP FOR WORKING PEOPLE, AND
THAT WAS THE BIG CHANGE FOR ME.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I WANT YOU TO MEET -- -- THIS
IS ERIC JEMBA, A SOPHOMORE FROM
HARVARD.
YOU CAN TELL FROM HIS
SWEATSHIRT.
>> GREAT SWEATSHIRT.
>> A FORMER INTERN FOR CORY
BOOKER.
HE'S CURRENTLY UNDECIDED WHO TO
SUPPORT.
>> HI.
>> ENTITLEMENTS, THOUGH NOT THE
SEXIEST ISSUE TO BE DISCUSSING.
DO YOU HAVE A PLAN TO REFORM OUR
PRESENT SOCIAL SECURITY TO
INCREASE ITS LONG GEFT?
>> I'M REALLY GLAD YOU ASKED
ABOUT SOCIAL SECURITY BECAUSE
THIS IS ONE THAT REMINDS YOU HOW
THINGS HAVE BROKEN APART IN THIS
COUNTRY.
AS YOU ALTHOUGH, SOCIAL SECURITY
PASSED BACK DURING THE GREAT
DEPR
DEPRESSION.
IT WAS TOO NARROW AND CUT OUT
TOO MANY -- PARTICULARLY, JOBS
UP THERE TO BE HELD BUT SOCIAL
SECURITY BECAME A MAINSTAY.
AND FROM THE 1930s UNTIL THE
LATE 1980s WE UNDERSTOOD THAT
SOCIAL SECURITY IS NOT SOMETHING
YOU CAN SET ONCE AND GO.
GOING BACK TO WORK CHANGES, HOW
MANY PEOPLE GET SICK, RIGHT?
AND SO EVERY FEW YEARS FOR A
VERY LONG TIME WE KEPT MAKING
LITTLE ADJUSTMENTS, AND THAT WAY
SOCIAL SECURITY STAYED ON A
TRACK TO MAKE SURE THAT IT WOULD
BE THERE FOR YOUR GENERATION AND
THE NEXT GENERATION AND THE NEXT
GENERATION AFTER THAT.
IN THE LATE 1980s THE
REPUBLICANS JUST SAID, NO, THAT
WE'RE NOT GOING TO MAKE ANYMORE
CHANGES.
NOT GOING TO KEEP THE CHANGES.
THE CONSEQUENCE IS EVERY TIME WE
GET IT DOWN IT'S A LITTLE
FURTHER OUT OF WHACK.
THE GOOD NEWS IS WE'VE GOT
ROUGHLY -- I HAVEN'T CHECKED THE
NUMBERS.
ABOUT 20 MORE YEARS WHERE WE ARE
IF WE DO NOTHING.
WHEN IT DROPS, IT WOULD DROP BY
ROUGHLY 25% AND THEN LEVEL OUT
AND BE THERE.
SO IT'S NOT THAT IT WILL
DISAPPEAR FOR YOUR GENERATION.
HERE'S THE DEAL.
THIS IS ONE MORE OF THOSE
PROBLEMS, A LITTLE LIKE CLIMATE,
THE SOONER YOU FIX IT, THE
EASIER IT IS TO FIX.
NOW IT'S ALREADY HARD ON THIS
FRONT BUT IT'S ONE OF THESE
THINGS WE NEED TO FIX NOW.
BUT THE PROBLEM WE'VE GOT, NOT
THAT NOBODY UNDERSTANDS --
>> WELL, NOT EVERYBODY
UNDERSTANDS THE MATH.
THERE ARE A WHOLE LOT OF PEOPLE
WHO UNDERSTAND THE MATH.
THE PROBLEM IS THE POLITICAL
WILL AND THE WILLINGNESS TO STEP
UP AND SAY, WE'VE GOT TO MAKE
ADJUSTMENTS.
WE HAVE TO MAKE ADJUSTMENTS -- I
BELIEVE WE NEED TO BEND THE
CURVES THEY'RE CALLED SO THAT
PARTICULARLY WOMEN WHO HAD LOWER
EARNINGS FOR SO MANY YEARS THAT
THEY WERE WORKING GET BETTER
SUPPORT IN THEIR LATER YEARS,
BUT AT THIS MOMENT THERE'S NO
POLITICAL WILL TO COME TOGETHER.
THERE'S NO ONE WILLING TO DRIVE
THIS.
WHY?
BECAUSE WASHINGTON KEEPS WORKING
FOR THOSE AT THE TOP.
IT'S NOT WORKING FOR PEOPLE WHO
ARE RELYING ON SOCIAL SECURITY.
YOUR QUESTION WAS IS THIS
SOMETHING -- THE PLAN IS NOT
HARD.
IT'S POLITICAL WILL TO MAKE IT
HAPPEN.
I'M WILLING TO TAKE ON THAT
FIGHT.
IT'S AN IMPORTANT FIGHT.
SO THANK YOU.
THANKS FOR THE QUESTION.
>> NEXT QUESTION COMES FROM MATT
SPRANT.
HE TOOK A LEAVE OF ABSENCE FROM
COLLEGE TO WORK AS A FULL-TIME
STAFFER FOR HILLARY CLINTON IN
THE 2016 CAMPAIGN.
>> HI, MAX.
>> SENATOR WARREN, I WANT TO SAY
THANK YOU FOR YOUR SERVICE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> MY QUESTION HAS TO DO WITH
THE POLITICS OF THIS RACE.
IN PARTICULAR, I KNOW THAT YOU
HAVE EXPERIENCED PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S NAME-CALLING AND
BULLYING FIRSTHAND AND GIVEN THE
SUCCESS THAT HE'S HAD WITH THESE
TACTICS IN THE PAST, I WAS
WONDERING HOW YOU WOULD PROPOSE
TO COUNTER THEM IF YOU WERE TO
BECOME THE DEMOCRATIC NOMINEE.
IN PARTICULAR, ARE YOU AFRAID HE
CAN CARICATURE YOU?
>> SO, THANKS FOR THE QUESTION.
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN AROUND THIS
BLOCK BEFORE.
BACK IN 2012 WHEN I RAN AGAINST
THAT VERY POPULAR REPUBLICAN
INCUMBENT.
HE RAN THE SAME PLAY AND WHAT I
DISCOVERED AT THAT POINT IS
AROUND THE COMMONWEALTH PEOPLE
CARE A WHOLE LOT MORE ABOUT
THEIR FAMILIES THAN THEY DO
ABOUT SOME KIND OF NAME-CALLING.
I GOT IN THE RACE IN '12 AND I
GOT IN THIS RACE RIGHT NOW AS A
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE NOT
BECAUSE I LOOKED AT MYSELF IN
THE MER ROHR EVERY DAY.
OH, SENATOR, PRESIDENT?
IT WASN'T THAT AT ALL.
IT'S MY LIFE'S WORK.
I GREW UP IN A FAMILY THAT WAS
PAYCHECK TO PAYCHECK.
I WAS ONE OF THOSE KIDS WHO HAD
A DREAM.
WE TALKED ABOUT COLLEGE.
I'VE KNOWN WHAT I'VE WANDED TO
DO SINCE SECOND GRADE.
>> HAVE WE HEARD FROM ERICA'S
PUBLIC SCHOOL TEACHERS?
COME ON, GUYS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I KNEW WHAT I WANTED TO DO.
BUT THERE WAS NO MONEY IN MY
FAMILY.
BY THE TIME I GRADUATED FROM
HIGH SCHOOL, THERE WAS NO MONEY
EVEN FOR COLLEGE APPLICATION
MUCH LESS TO SEND ME OFF TO FOUR
YEARS OF COLLEGE.
I HAVE A TWISTED STORY.
LIKE SOME AMERICANS DO.
WE'RE NOT ALL ON A STATE LINE.
THE GOOD NEWS IS I WON A
SCHOLARSHIP, YEAH.
AND THEN AT 19 I FELL IN LOVE.
YEAH.
AND THEN I GOT MARRIED.
THEN I DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL,
YEAH.
AND I TOOK A JOB ANSWERING
PHONES, AND I THOUGHT THAT WAS
GOING TO BE MY LIFE FOREVER.
A GOOD LIFE, BUT NOT THE DREAM I
HAD.
AND THEN I FOUND A COMMUTER
COLLEGE THAT COST $50 A
SEMESTER, AND FOR A PRICE THAT I
COULD PAY FOR ON A PART-TIME
WAITRESSING JOB, I HAD A CHANCE
TO GET A FOUR YEAR DIPLOMA AND
BECOME A SPECIAL NEEDS TEACHER.
I HAD LIVED MY DREAM.
AND THAT'S WHAT I BELIEVE IS THE
BEST OF AMERICA, WHEN WE OPEN
MORE DOORS FOR MORE PEOPLE.
I WANT TO LIVE IN AN AMERICA
THAT'S NOT JUST ABOUT BORN
OPPORTUNITY BUT THAT'S FOR
OPPORTUNITY FOR ALL OF US.
JUST THOSE FEW PIECES I PUT
TOMPGT A 2 CENT WEALTH TAX WOULD
LET US DO UNIVERSAL CHILD CARE,
WOULD LET US DO UNIVERSAL PRE-K,
WOULD LET US NOT BACK THE
STUDENT LOAN DEBT BURDEN AND
STILL HAVE MONEY TO SEND.
I THINK THIS IS THE PACE WE'VE
GOT TO MAKE AGAINST DONALD
TRUMP.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO WIN BY SAYING
NOT DONALD TRUMP.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO WIN BY DOING
BETTER NAME-CALLING THAN HE
DOES.
THE WAY WE'RE GOING TO DO THIS,
WE'RE GOING TO GET OUT AND TALK
ABOUT OUR VISION AND HOW IT
AFFECTS FAMILIES ALL ACROSS THE
COUNTRY AND WE'RE GOING TO
INVITE PEOPLE NOT JUST TO VOTE
BUT TO COME OFF THE SIDELINES
AND BE PART OF THIS.
TO GET ENGAGED.
TO VOLUNTEER, TO KICK IN FIVE
BUCKS TO GO TO EE LIT BEZ W
WARREN.
WHAT'S AT STAKE IS NOT ONLY OUR
ECONOMIC FUTURE, IT IS ALSO OUR
DEMOCRACY.
I'M IN THIS FIGHT ALL THE WAY.
I THINK WE MAKE THAT CASE AND I
THINK THE PEOPLE ARE WITH US.
>> WE'LL HAVE MORE.
STAY WITH US.
It's Cedar Plank Seafood time
at Red Lobster!
Featuring three new dishes that
are planked-to-perfection.
Feast on NEW Cedar-Plank
Lobster & Shrimp.
Or NEW Colossal Shrimp & Salmon
with a citrusy drizzle.
Tender, smoky, and together
on one plank...
...but not for long-
so hurry in!
♪♪
[laughter]
"I'm okay."
♪♪
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
♪
Thanks to Priceline
working with top airlines
to turn their unsold seats
into amazing deals,
family reunion attendance is up.
We're all related!
Yeah, I see it.
And because Priceline
offers great deals
by comparing thousands
of prices in real time,
sports fans are seeing
more away games.
Various:
Yeah-h-h!
Is that safe?
Oh, y...
Ahh!
Not at all.
No, ma'am.
Nope.
And more people than ever are
enjoying romantic getaways.
(Romantic music)
That's gross
Priceline.
Every trip is a big deal.
■Ñ■■■çl■
>>> WELCOME BACK.
WE'RE LIVE IN NEW HAMPSHIRE FOR
A SPECIAL CNN DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL TOWN HALL.
SENATOR ELIZABETH WARREN FROM
MASSACHUSETTS.
I WANT TO -- OUR NEXT QUESTION
IS ABOUT CLIMATE CHANGE.
>> GOOD.
>> YOU TALKED ABOUT IT BRIEFLY.
IT'S DRASTICALLY GROWN IN A POLL
TODAY.
THIS IS TYELER PIERCE.
HE'S STUDYING BIOMEDICAL
SCIENCE, WHICH I'M INTO THE EVEN
SURE WHAT THAT MEANS, BECAUSE
I'M DUMB.
HE WORKED AS A FELLOW FOR THE
NEW HAMPSHIRE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
MID TERMS.
>> HI, SENATOR, HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M GOOD.
>> WHAT WILL YOU DO TO COMBAT
CLIMATE CHANGE?
>> TYLER, IT IS THE EXISTENTIAL
QUESTION RIGHT NOW.
AS I SAID, I WAS JUST OUT IN
THREE DIFFERENT STATES FACING
CLIMATE -- THE EFFECTS OF
CLIMATE CHANGE IN DIFFERENT WAYS
BUT ALL OF THEM POTENTIALLY
DEVASTATING.
I HAVE AN 8-YEAR-OLD GRANDSON
AND I THINK ABOUT WHAT THE WORLD
IS GOING TO BE LIKE WHEN HE'S
38.
WILL IT BE A PLACE WHERE THE
MIDWEST HAS BURNED UP?
WHERE WE HAVE LOST OUR GREAT
FORESTS?
WILL IT BE A PLACE WHERE LARGE
PARTS OF THE OCEANS ARE DEAD?
WILL IT BE A PLACE WHERE PEOPLE
AROUND THE WORLD ARE JUST
FIGHTING FOR CLEAN WATER?
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME TO
MAKE A CHANGE.
WE MUST MAKE CHANGE AND WE MUST
MAKE IT NOW.
SO HERE'S HOW I SEE THIS.
I AM A STRONG SUPPORTER OF GREEN
NEW DEAL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I WANT TO TELL YOU WHY.
THERE'S TWO PRINCIPLE REASONS
FOR THAT.
THE FIRST REASON THAT I'M A
STRONG SUPPORTER IS ITS A WAY
FOR URGENCY.
WE CANNOT WAIT LONGER.
WE HAVE TO MAKE CHANGE.
THAT'S HOW I HEAR THIS.
THE SECOND PART ABOUT THE GREEN
NEW DEAL IS THAT IT CALLS FOR A
HUGE INVESTMENT IN OUR
INFRASTRUCTURE AND I THINK
THAT'S JUST ABSOLUTELY CRITICAL.
AND WHEN I SAY OUR
INFRASTRUCTURE IT'S ABOUT OUR
POWER INFRASTRUCTURE BUT ALSO
ABOUT HARDENING OUR
INFRASTRUCTURE SO THAT WE CAN
WITH STAND THE STORM AND MOVE TO
POWER.
LOTS OF PIECES THAT WE NEED TO
DO BUT I ALSO SEE THIS AS A TIME
WHEN IT'S ALL HANDS ON DECK.
THAT IS WE NEED TO DO EVERYTHINA
LET ME JUST DO A COUPLE THAT THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
CAN DO ALL BY HERSELF.
I JUST PUT OUT A PLAN ON FIRST
DAY OF MY ADMINISTRATION I WILL
PUT IN PLACE A MORITORIUM.
NO NEW DRILLING, NO NEW MINING
ON FEDERAL LANDS, PERIOD.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WE SHOULD NOT BE SELLING OUT
FOR PENNIES ON THE DOLLAR TO
MINING COMPANIES AND TO OIL
COMPANIES OUR NATIONAL
TREASURES.
I'LL GIVE YOU ANOTHER LITTLE
PIECE OF THIS AND THAT IS 10,000
JOBS.
FOR PEOPLE THAT WANT TO SPEND A
YEAR IN THE NATIONAL PARKS AND
NATIONAL FORESTS TO BE ABLE TO
GIVE SOMETHING BACK TO THE LAND
AND MAKE REPAIRS.
THIS IS A PART OF WHAT WE CAN DO
TOGETHER.
HOW ABOUT A COUPLE OF MORE
PIECES?
THE UNITED STATES IS A WORLD
LEADER ON CLIMATE.
WE ARE.
WE'RE JUST LEADING IN THE WRONG
DIRECTION NOW.
THAT'S DANGEROUS BECAUSE IT'S
NOT ONLY WHAT WE'RE DOING WRONG
BUT WE'RE GIVING COVER TO THE
REST OF THE WORLD.
FOR EVERYBODY THAT DOESN'T WANT
TO TAKE THE TOUGH STEPS AND
DOESN'T WANT TO MAKE CHANGES.
WE'RE GIVING THEM COVER.
WE BECOME A WORLD LEADER IN THE
DIRECTION OF A SUSTAINABLE
EARTH.
CAN I THROW IN ONE MORE?
THAT'S NO COAL LOBBISTS ARE HEAD
OF THE EPA.
>> ONE MORE QUESTION FROM THE
AUDIENCE.
>> HI, NICHOLAS.
>> AS A DEMOCRAT THAT HAS A LOT
OF RESPECT AND ADMIRATION FOR
PRESIDENT OBAMA BUT THINKS LIKE
EVERY PRESIDENT HE HAD HIS
SHORTCOMINGS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS THE
PHILOSOPHICAL DIFFERENCE IN THE
WAY THAT YOU WOULD APPROACH YOUR
JOB AS PRESIDENT AND THE WAY
PRESIDENT OBAMA APPROACHED HIS
JOB?
>> I'M GOING TO TAKE IT IN A
LITTLE BIT DIFFERENT DIRECTION
IF I CAN.
NO, NO, I'M GOING TO GET HERE.
SO I SPENT AS I TOLD ALL OF YOU
REALLY MY WHOLE LIFE'S WORK INTO
WHAT'S HAPPENING WITH WORKING
FAMILIES.
STARTING IN THE EARLY 2000S, THE
CRISIS WAS COMING.
I WAS WAVING MY ARM, RINGING THE
BELL, DOING EVERYTHING I COULD.
I SAID FAMILIES ARE GETTING
CHEATED ALL OVER THIS COUNTRY.
IT START WHEN THE MORTGAGE
COMPANIES TARGETED COMMUNITIES
OF COLOR.
THEY TARGETED SENIORS.
THEY TARGETED LATINOS.
THEY CAME IN AND TARGETED THE
WORST OUT OF THE COMMUNITIES AND
TALKED ABOUT IT TO ANYONE THAT
WOULD LISTEN A CRISIS IS COMING.
IF YOUR EARS ARE STUFFED WITH
MONEY IT'S HARD TO HEAR.
SO THE CRISIS HIT IN 2007-2008
AND JUST TOOK US DOWN.
THE BIG QUESTION IS WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO GOING FORWARD?
A LOT OF FOLKS WHAT WE SHOULD DO
IS JUST TAKE CARE OF THE BIG
FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONS.
WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE THAT THIS
NEVER HAPPENS TO WORKING
FAMILIES AGAIN.
SO THE IDEA I HAD, CONSUMER
FINANCIAL PROTECTION BUREAU, I
SAID I'M GOING TO GET IN THIS
FIGHT.
I'M A COLLEGE PROFESSOR.
I HAVE NO POLITICAL SWAY BUT I'M
GOING TO GET IN THIS FIGHT AND
FIGHT FOR IT.
PEOPLE TOLD ME TWO THINGS.
GREAT IDEA.
DON'T EVEN TRY.
THE REASON NOT TO TRY IS THERE'S
NO WAY ON GOD'S GREEN EARTH
YOU'LL EVER GET THIS PASSED
BECAUSE THE GIANT FINANCIAL
INSTITUTIONS WILL FIGHT YOU
EVERY INCH OF THE WAY.
>> WE HAVE TO WRAP IT UP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO HERE'S WHAT HAPPENED.
I GOT IN THE FIGHT.
PRESIDENT OBAMA SIGNED IT INTO
LAW AND HE WAS THE ONE WHO STOOD
THERE WHEN EVERYONE ELSE SAID IN
HIS ADMINISTRATION THROW THAT
AGENCY UNDER THE BUS AND HE SAID
NO I'M NOT GOING TO LET THIS
CRISIS PASS AND NOT COME AWAY
WITH A CONSUMER AGENCY THAT
MAKES SURE THAT FAMILIES EVER
GET CHEATED AGAIN.
I'LL ALWAYS BE GRATEFUL TO THE
PRESIDENT FOR THAT.
>> UP NEXT, VERMONT SENATOR,
BERNIE SANDERS.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ APPLAUSE ]
If your moderate to severe
ulcerative colitis
or Crohn's symptoms...
are holding you back...
and your
current treatment
hasn't worked
well enough...
it may be
time for a change.
Ask your doctor
about ENTYVIO®,
the only biologic
developed and approved
just for UC and Crohn's.
ENTYVIO® works at the
site of inflammation
in the GI tract,
and is clinically proven
to help many patients
achieve both symptom
relief and remission.
Infusion and serious
allergic reactions
can happen during
or after treatment.
ENTYVIO® may
increase risk of infection,
which ca.
PML, a rare, serious,
potentially fatal
brain infection
caused by a virus
may be possible.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection,
experience frequent
infections
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
ver problems  occu?■NTYVIO®.
experience frequent
infections
If your UC or
Crohn's ent