ó
So, you're open all day,
every day.
That's what 24/7 means, sugar.
Kind of like how you
get 24/7 access
to licensed agents with GEICO.
Hmm?
Yeah, you just go online,
or give them a call anytime.
You don't say.
Yep. Now what will it take
to get 24/7 access
to that lemon meringue pie?
PIE!
PIE'S COMING!
That's what it takes, baby.
GEICO®. Great service
from licensed agents, 24/7.
>>> THE 2020 DEMOCRATS, AMERICA
HILL, THANKS FOR JOINING US.
WE'RE SEEING THINGS WRAP UP
THERE IN MANCHESTER, NEW
HAMPSHIRE, MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIEG,
TAKING SELFIES, THE HOUR AHEAD
COMPLETE ANALYSIS OF CNN'S
DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL TOWN
HALL, FIVE CANDIDATES FOR
PRESIDENT ANSWERING THOSE
QUESTIONS FROM THE AUDIENCE,
WHICH AS WE SAID WAS MADE UP OF
STUDENTS, COLLEGE AGED VOTERS
PRESSING THESE DEMOCRATS ON A
VARIETY OF TOPICS, HEALTH CARE,
STUDENT DEBT, CRIMINAL JUSTICE
REFORM, CLIMATE CH SENATORS AMY
KLOBUCHAR, ELIZABETH WARREN,
BERNIE SANDERS, KAMALA HARRIS
AND MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIEG LEAVING
THE STAGE A FEW MINUTES AGO.
HOW DID THEY DO?
LET'S CHECK IN IN■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
NEW HAMPSHIRE.
MALIKA HENDERSON AND DAVID
GOOD TO HAVE YOU ALL WITH US
TONIGHT, A LOT OF ENERGY, DAVID
CHALIAN, IN THAT ROOM,CH
THEY■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
TO YOU FROM THESE CANDIDATES
TONIGHT?
>> THERE WERE A FEW THINGS THAT
STOOD OUT, ERICA, YOU MENTIONED
THEM IN SOME OF THE TOPICS.
I THOUGHT THE ANSWERS ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT, POST MUELLER REPORT
RELATING TO THE PRESIDENT REALLY
INTERESTING BECAUSE IT SEEMS
LIKE THERE'S A GROWING CHORUS
INSIDE THIS DEMOCRATIC
NOMINATING CONTEST FIELD THAT WE
HAVE OF THESE CANDIDATES FOR THE
IDEA OF THE HOUSE MOVING ALONG
IN THAT DIRECTION AT THE VERY
SAME TIME THAT NANCY PELOSI IS
SORT OF TRYING TO CAMP THAT
DOWN.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS INTERESTING
TO HEAR KAMALA HARRIS AND PETE
BUTTIGIEG ADVANCE.
I THOUGHT THERE WERE SURPRISES
IN THE NIGHT, WHETHER IT WAS
TALKING ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT
FELONS CURRENTLY SERVING THEIR
PRISON TERMS IN PRISON SHOULD BE
OF■■■■■EBATE IN THIS ##■■■■■ F■P
DING##■
OVERALL, I THINKERE RIGHT,
HEALTH CARE, COLLEGE
AFFORDAB SUES THAT THESE CANDID
HEAR■■■■■HEY GO ON
VOTERS, AHINK THIS■■■1Y TO THES
TO SPEAK TO■■■■■■■ AUDIENC■■■■
■■■    ■  ■■■■ ■ # ■ ■#■■■#111
WINNING COALITION# ■■■■ THE■##■
TOPICS FRONT O THEIR MIND WAS
IMPORTANT FOR THESE■■TES
TO DO.
>> CERTAINLY HEARD THA■■ IN
SOME OF THE
KLING IT VERY CLEAR
THAT WAS THE YOUTH, SHE SAID,
THEIR MOMENT THAT THEY GOT
DEMOCRATS THERE IN NOVEMBER.
I WANT TO PICK UP, THOUGH, ON
IMPEACHMENT, NIA-MALIKA, EACH
CANDIDATE WAS ASKED ABOUT THAT,
TO GET THROUGH THE ISSUES ON THE
CAMPAIGN TRAIL THEY HAVE TO GET
THROUGH THE QUESTIONS WHETHER
THEY WANT TO OR NOT.
WHAT SENATOR WARREN STUCK WITH A
LOT OF PEOPLE.
>> THERE IS NO POLITICAL
INCONVENIENCE EXCEPTION TO THE
UNITED STATES CONSTITUTION.
IF ANY OTHER HUMAN BEING IN THIS
COUNTRY HAD DONE WHAT'S
DOCUMENTED IN THE MUELLER REPORT
THEY WOULD BE ARRESTED AND PUT
IN JAIL.
IF THERE ARE PEOPLE IN THE HOUSE
OR THE SENATE WHO WANT TO SAY
THAT'S WHAT A PRESIDENT CAN DO
WHEN THE PRESIDENT IS BEING
INVESTIGATED FOR HIS OWN
WRONGDOINGS OR WHEN A FOREIGN
GOVERNMENT ATTACKS OUR COUNTRY
THEN THEY SHOULD HAVE TO TAKE
THAT VOTE AND LIVE WITH IT FOR
THE REST OF THEIR LIVES.
>> THAT LAST PART, WE ARE GOING
TO BE HEARING MORE OF THAT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> YOU SEE THE CROWD THERE
REACTING, CHEERING HER ON,
ELIZABETH WARREN IS PROBABLY THE
LEADER OF THE IDEAS PRIMARY, SHE
HASN'T CAUGHT ON JUST YET IN
TERMS OF POLLS AND FUND RAISING
BUT THERE WITH THAT ANSWER SHE
IS GOING TO BE ECHOED BY A LOT
OF PROGRESSIVES.
WE SEE IN THE HOUSE ALREADY
SAYING THEY WANT IMPEACHMENT.
CERTAINLY GRASS ROOTS VOTERS AS
WELL WHO WANT TO SEE
IMPEACHMENT.
I THOUGHT SHE ARTICULATED IT
QUITE WELL, QUITE CLEARLY IN THE
WAY SHE HAS DONE WITH OTHER
POLICY ISSUES, BREAKING UP THE
BIG TECH COMPANIES, BOLD POLICY
SHE HAS, FOR INSTANCE, ON
COLLEGE LOAN DEBT.
SO WE'LL SEE.
I MEAN, I THINK SHE SET A REAL
LINE IN THE SAND AND SHE DID
THIS EARLIER, SHE'S BEEN THE ONE
WHO CAME OUT REALLY EARLY AND
SAID IMPEACHMENT AFTER SHE READ
THE MUELLER REPORT AND YOU SEE
THERE WHERE KLOBUCHAR WAS, SHE'S
LIKE, IT'S NOT UP TO ME.
>> SHE SAID I'M ON THE JURY.
>> YEAH, IT'S UP TO THE HOUSE,
EXACTLY.
>> AND YOU SAW KAMALA HARRIS
COMING OUT FURTHER THAN SHE'D
COME OUT BEFORE IN TERMS OF
IMPEACHMENT, BUT ALSO SAYING
LET'S BE PRACTICAL ABOUT THIS,
IT WOULDN'T HAPPEN IN THE
SENATE.
>> AND IT CAME A BIT FROM BERNIE
SANDERS.
I WANTED TO PLAY WHAT THEY BOTH
HAD TO SAY AND PICK UP ON THAT.
>> DO YOU BELIEVE ANYTHING
YOU'VE READ AND PROCESSED IN
THAT REPORT COULD HAVE THE WORD
IMPEACHABLE ATTACHED TO IT?
>> ANY -- FIRST OF ALL, I
BELIEVE I'M THE JURY HERE, I'M
NOT GOING TO PREDISPOSE THINGS.
I'M NOT SAYING IT IS OR IT
ISN'T.
THERE'S VERY DISTURBING THINGS
THAT WOULD LEAD YOU TO BELIEVE
THERE'S OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
>> HERE IS MY CONCERN, AT THE
END OF THE DAY WHAT IS MOST
IMPORTANT TO ME IS TO SEE THAT
DONALD TRUMP IS NOT REELECTED
PRESIDENT.
I INTEND TO DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO MAKE SURE THAT DOESN'T
HAPPEN.
BUT IF -- AND THIS IS AN IF.
IF FOR THE NEXT YEAR, YEAR AND A
HALF GOING RIGHT INTO THE HEART
OF THE ELECTION ALL THAT THE
CONGRESS IS TALKING ABOUT IS
IMPEACHING TRUMP, AND TRUMP,
TRUMP, TRUMP, AND MUELLER,
MUELLER, MUELLER, WHAT I WORRY
ABOUT IS THAT WORKS TO TRUMP'S
ADVANTAGE.
>> YOU KNOW --
>> GOT A POINT.
>> NO, AND IT WAS QUITE THE
CONTRAST.
FIRST OF ALL, ELIZABETH WARREN
HAS -- I HAVE NO DOUBT THAT SHE
BELIEVES WHAT SHE SAID.
SHE ALSO UNDERSTANDS THAT THERE
MAY BE POLITICAL ADVANTAGE TO
IT.
SHE'S HAD A HARD TIME GETTING
HER CAMPAIGN GOING HERE.
SHE'S BEEN LEADING ON IDEAS, NOT
LEADING IN TERMS OF MONEY, NOT
LEADING IN TERMS OF POLLS AND
THIS CLEARLY IS SOMETHING SHE
HOPES WILL IGNITE PEOPLE ON THE
LEFT.
SHE'S IN A BIT OF A COMPETITION
WITH BERNIE SANDERS FOR SOME OF
THOSE VOTES.
IN HIS ANSWER WHAT YOU SAW IS
PART OF THE KEY TO HIS APPEAL
WHICH IS HIS LASER LIKE FOCUS ON
ECONOMIC ISSUES AND ECONOMIC
POPULISM.
SHE TOO, A POPULIST, BUT HE HAS
REALLY CORNERED THAT AND HE'S
BASICALLY SAYING YOU KNOW WHAT
THESE ECONOMIC ISSUES THAT ARE
CLOSE TO PEOPLE'S LIVES THAT'S
WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT, THAT'S
NUMBER ONE ON MY AGENDA.
SO DIFFERENT APPROACHES.
>> INTERESTING, TOO, WHEN WE
HEAR FROM KAMALA HARRIS.
AND I WANT TO PLAY HER RESPONSE
TO THAT QUESTION.
>> I BELIEVE CONGRESS SHOULD
TAKE THE STEPS TOWARDS
IMPEACHMENT.
I'VE NOT SEEN ANY EVIDENCE SINCE
I'VE BEEN IN THE UNITED STATES
SENATE THAT THE UNITED STATES
SENATE AND THE REPUBLICANS HOLD
THE MAJORITY, I'VE NOT SEEN ANY
EVIDENCE TO SUGGEST THAT THEY
WILL WEIGH ON THE FACTS INSTEAD
OF ON PARTISAN ADHERENCE TO
BEING PROTECTIVE OF THIS
PRESIDENT AND THAT'S WHAT
CONCERNS ME AND WHAT WILL BE THE
EVENTUAL OUTCOME.
WE HAVE TO BE REALISTIC ABOUT
WHAT MIGHT BE THE END RESULT BUT
THAT DOESN'T MEAN THE PROCESS
SHOULD NOT TAKE HOLD.
>> THE PROCESS SHOULD TAKE HOLD,
DAVID CHALIAN, CONGRESS SHOULD
TAKE THE STEPS, IS THERE A
SLIGHT SHIFT THERE?
>> OH, DEFINITELY.
I MEAN, JUST OVER THE WEEKEND
SHE WAS ASKED ABOUT THIS AND DID
NOT GO TO THIS PLACE OF SAYING
THAT THE HOUSE SHOULD TAKE
STEPS.
IEEE■■■■■■E■EEEEE■■■■■ DAVID AX
HIT O SOMETHING THERE WHICH IS
KAMALA HARRIS IS SHOWING US SHE
TOO DETERMINES IT'S PROBABLY
SMARTER POLITICS T IN
TERMS OF ENLIVENING THE
PROGRESSIVE OF THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY TO MOVE IN THIS
POSITION OF SAYING,Y, THE
HOUSE SHOULD START THIS.
AND WITHOUT, BY THE##))#■#■■#■■
POLITICAL DOWNSIDE FOR THESE
FOLKS TO TAKE THATOSITION.RE OU
THAT WAY.O HEARD BUTTIGIEG MOVEL
THIS UP TOUSE AND THE TE BUT HEE
AFTER REVIEWING T MUEPORT TO SA
DO SOMETHING.
THAT SEEMS TO ME A POLITICAL
PLAY THAT THESE DEMOCRATSAVE
DETERMINED IS A WAY TO ENLIVEN
THE BASE WITHOUT REALLY MUCH
RISK OF ANYTHING -- ANY DOWNSIDE
FOR THEIR CAMPAIGN AND QUITE
FRANKLY AS KAMALA HARRIS IS
SAYING WITHOUT THE NOTION THAT
DONALD TRUMP IS REALLY IN DANGER
OF BEING PUSHED OUT OF OFFICE IN
SOME WAY.
>> TO YOUR POINT, THOUGH, ON THE
LANGUAGE THAT SENATOR HARRIS
USED IS REAL INTERESTING.
SHE IS A VERY ACCOMPLISHED
LAWYER AND SHE GIVES A LOT OF
LAWYERLY ANSWERS.
AND THAT WAS LAWYERLY LANGUAGE.
NOT HE SHOULD BE IMPEACHED, WE
SHOULD TAKE THE STEPS TOWARDS
IMPEACHMENT WITH A DISCLAIMER
THAT THE SENATE PROBABLY
WOULDN'T ACT ON IT AND THERE
WERE AT LEAST FOUR OTHER
OCCASIONS DURING HER ANSWERS
WHEN SHE WAS ASKED ABOUT TOUGH
QUESTIONS, REPARATIONS, VOTING
ON THE PART OF PRISONERS WHERE
HER ANSWER WAS, WELL, WE SHOULD
HAVE THAT CONVERSATION.
THAT'S A DISCUSSION WE SHOULD
HAVE.
AND I THINK THAT AT SOME POINT
THIS COULD END UP BEING A
PROBLEM.
SHE IS AN INCREDIBLY COMPELLING
PERSONALITY, VERY BRIGHT AND
ACCOMPLISHED PERSON BUT SHE'S
VERY CAUTIOUS AND THAT CAUTION
WAS PRETTY APPARENT IN A LOT OF
HER ANSWERS TONIGHT.
>> IT'S INTERESTING WHEN YOU
LOOK THE JUXTAPOSITION WITH HER
ANSWERS ON VOTING RIGHTS FOR
CONVICTED COMMONS BEHIND BARS
VERSUS WHAT WE HEARD FROM PETE
BUTTIGIEG, ALL OF THAT CAME
AFTER THE FIRST PERSON TO REALLY
TALK ABOUT THIS AND THIS WAS A
MOMENT THAT NO ONE SAW COMING,
BUT IT'S CERTAINLY HAVING A
MOMENT TONIGHT.
LET'S LISTEN TO WHAT BERNIE
SANDERS HAD TO SAY ON THAT
QUESTION.
>> I THINK THE RIGHT TO VOTE IS
INHERENT TO OUR DEMOCRACY.
YES, EVEN FOR TERRIBLE PEOPLE
BECAUSE ONCE YOU START CHIPPING
AWAY AND YOU SAY THAT GUY
COMMITTED A TERRIBLE CRIME, NOT
GOING TO LET HIM VOTE, OH, THAT
PERSON DID THAT, NOT GOING TO
LET THAT PERSON VOTE, YOU'RE
RUNNING DOWN A SLIPPERY SLOPE.
>> MY FOLLOW-UP QUESTION GOES TO
THIS, YOU'RE WRITING AN
OPPOSITION ED AGAINST YOU LIKE
YOU'RE SAYING THE BOSTON
MARATHON BOMBER SHOULD VOTE, NOT
AFTER HE PAYS HIS DEBT IN
SOCIETY, BUT WHILE HE'S IN JAIL.
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
>> CHRIS, I'VE WRITTEN MANY 30
SECOND OPPOSITION ADS THROUGHOUT
HI LIFE.
THIS WILL BE JUST ANOTHER ONE.
>> THERE IS A QUESTION ABOUT
WHETHER OR NOT THIS IS
OPPOSITION AD GOAL, THIS WOULD
PERHAPS WORK VERY WELL AND IT
IS.
BUT --
>> LET'S STIPULATE.
>> BUT THE RESPONSE IS, WHEN
PETE BAA UTTIGIEG, HE WAS ASKED
ANDERSON, I DON'T THINK TO THINK
ABOUT IT, I'M CLEAR, AFTER
THEY'VE DONE IT, THEY'VE SERVED
THEIR TIME, MY ANSWER IS YES.
>> I THINK SENATOR SANDERS IS ON
THE WRONG POLITICAL END OF THAT
ISSUE.
PART OF HIS APPEAL, HOWEVER, IS
THAT HE JUST APPEARS TO BE A GUY
WHO'S SPEAKING HIS MIND, HE'S
NOT MAKING CALCULATIONS.
AND THAT'S PART OF IT.
PART OF BUTTIGIEG'S APPEAL, AND
CERTAINLY THAT WAS APPARENT IN
THAT ANSWER WAS HE ANSWERED
DIRECTLY.
THERE'S AN ANSWER THAT'S YES OR
NO.
AND HE SAID NO AND HE EXPLAINED
THAT WHEN YOU'RE IN PRISON
YOU'RE THERE AND IT'S A
PUNISHMENT AND YOU MAKE
SACRIFICES.
YOU'RE SACRIFICING YOUR FREEDOM
AND THIS IS ONE OF THE
SACRIFICES YOU HAVE TO MAKE.
I SUSPECT HE'D WIN THAT DEBATE
BUT BOTH OF THEM PROBABLY GOT
CREDIT FOR NOT EQUIVOCATING
ABOUT THE QUESTION.
>> AND THE RNC WAS OUT PRETTY
IMMEDIATELY AFTER KAMALA
HARRIS'S EQUIVOCATION WITH AN
EMAIL, THE SUBJECT IS KAMALA
WANTS TO HAVE A CONVERSATION
ABOUT THE BOSTON MARATHON BOMBER
VOTING.
RIGHT?
SO IT IS GOING TO BE AN ISSUE
MAYBE FOR HER, OR JUST AN
EQUIVOCATION, ESSENTIALLY SAYING
OH THIS IS SOMETHING I NEED TO
THINK ABOUT.
>> SHE MIGHT SOLACE IN THE
FACT THEY THOUGHT SHE WAS WORTHY
OF THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, MARIO CUOMO, THE
LATE GOVERNOR OF NEW YORK USED
TO SAY THE ONLY PLACE THEY SHOOT
BACKWARDS IS IN COWBOY MOVIES,
MEANING IF YOU'RE AHEAD, THEY'RE
SHOOTING AT YOU, IF YOU'RE NOT,
NOBODY IS GOING AFTER YOU.
>> SHE'S A TARGET, THAT'S GOOD.
>> SHE CAN TAKE SATISFACTION IN
KNOWING THAT SHE'S ON THEIR
RADAR SCREEN.
>> THAT'S A LOVELY PLACE TO STOP
OUR CONVERSATION BRIEFLY.
WE'LL PICK IT UP.
STAY WITH ME EVERYONE, THESE
FIVE DEMOCRATS TAKING QUESTIONS
TONIGHT FROM COLLEGE AGED
STUDENTS IN A SERIES OFPRESIDEN.
OUR COVERAGE CONTINUES.
JUST AHEAD.
♪
Allergies with sinus
congestion and pressure?
You won't find relief here.
♪
Go to the pharmacy counter
for powerful Claritin-D.
While the leading allergy spray
only relieves 6 symptoms,
Claritin-D relieves 8, including
sinus congestion and pressure.
Claritin-D relieves more.
♪♪
AHHHH!
We're here.
♪♪
■#■■#■#■■■■
ñC
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
So in this commercial we see
two travelers
at a Comfort INN with a glow
around them,
so people watching will be like,
"Wow, maybe I'll glow too
if I book direct at
ChoiceHotels.com."
Who glows?
Just say, Badda Book.
Badda Boom.
Book now at ChoiceHotels.com.
■■■■■w■■;Ñ;ñ■/■
♪ ♪
Plants capture CO2.
What if other kinds of plants
captured it too?■C■1■1
If these industrial plants had
technologyçg■g■g■g■gk
we could help lower emissions.
Carbon Capture is important
technology -
and experts agree.
That's why we're working on ways
to improve it.
So plants...
can be a little more...
like plants.
♪ ♪■
Who's idea was this?
♪
>>> ONE WAY TO STAND OUT OF
VOTERS IS ACTUALLY PRE PRETTY
SIMPLE, GIVE SPECIFICS.
THE AUDIENCE QUESTIONS TONIGHT
ASKING FOR THEM, HITTING ON
SEVERAL ISSUES FROM HEALTH CARE
TO VETERANS, CLIMATE CHANGE TO
STUDENT DEBT AND VOTING RIGHTS.
BACK WITH DAVID CHALIAN,
NIA-MALIKA HENDERSON AND DAVID
AXELROD.
ONE OF THE THINGS THAT STOOD OUT
WITH MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIEG ANDER
COOPER PUSHED HIM ON THE LACK OF
SPECIFICS HE'S LAID OUT ON HIS
WEBSITE.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> I ALSO THINK IT'S IMPORTANT
WE NOT DROWN PEOPLE WITH MINUTIA
BEFORE WE'VE VINDICATED THE
VALUES THAT ANIMATE OUR
POLICIES.
AS DEMOCRATS THIS IS -- WE
EXPECT PEOPLE TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
OUR VALUES MUST BE FROM THAT.
I EXPECT THAT IT WILL BE VERY
EASY AND CLEAR TO TELL WHERE I
STAND ON EVERY SPECIFIC POLICY
CHALLENGE OF OUR TIME, BUT I'M
GOING TO TAKE THE TIME TO LAY
THAT OUT WHILE ALSO TALKING
ABOUT VALUES AND EVERYDAY
IMPACTS.
>> HE'S GOING TO TAKE A LITTLE
TIME.
HE'S GOING TO FIGURE IT OUT.
HE'LL GET BACK.
IS THAT -- I MEAN, IS THAT THE
RIGHT ANSWER TONIGHT?
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S THE ONLY
ANSWER HE HAS.
AT THIS POINT.
I GUESS AT SOME POINT HE WAS
SAYING WELL THERE'S GOING TO BE
SOMETHING ON THE WEBSITE WHERE
YOU CAN DO A SEARCH TO SEE HOW I
FEEL ABOUT SOMETHING.
>> THEN IT WAS THERE.
WE CONFIRMED IT HAD BEEN ADDED.
>> THIS IS A PROBLEM BETO
O'ROURKE HAS HAD, WHERE IS THE
BEEF TO YOUR SOARING RHETORIC?
IN MANY WAYS BETO O'ROURKE IS
BETTER AT THE SOARING RHETORIC,
THE VALUES, AND EXPLAINING THE
VALUES IN THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
THAN PETE BUTTIGIEG IS.
PETE BUTTIGIEG IS A TECH NOCRAT,
THERE WASN'T A LOT OF CONNECTION
EHE MADE WITH THE AUDIENCE
THERE, BETTER AT THE END.
IT WAS A BUNCH OF HARVARD KIDS,
AND HE WENT TO HARVARD.
SO, AGAIN, THIS -- HE WAS OUR --
IT WAS OUR FIVE.
SO MAYBE THE KIDS WERE A LITTLE
TIRED FROM SITTING THERE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, HE'S GOT TO WORK
ON THAT.
PARTICULARLY BECAUSE HE'S A
YOUNG GUY SO HE'S GOT TO COME
OUT, I THINK, WITH SOME POLICY
PRETTY QUICKLY.
>> HE'S BEEN ON A ROCKET RIDE
SINCE HIS FIRST CNN TOWN HALL
WHICH WAS REALLY HIS
INTRODUCTION TO THE COUNTRY AND
HE'S BEEN ON A VERY, VERY ENNER
H
-- ENGER JETTIC MEDIA BLITZ.
HE'S AT THAT POINT NOW.
HE HAS TO BEGIN TO LAY OUT SOME
OF THE PARTICULARS.
NOW, WE SHOULD POINT OUT THAT
MOST AMERICANS ARE NOT TUNED
INTO THIS RACE TO THAT DEGREE.
HE HAS TIME, JUST AS BETO
O'ROURKE HAS TIME, WE TEND TO
JUDGE THESE THINGS IN THE
MOMENT.
AND HE'S GOTTEN OFF TO A GREAT
START.
BUT THERE ARE LIMITS TO THAT
BOOSTER ROCKET STAGE AND HE'S
>> YOU KNOW, AS YOU'R
>> DA DON'T I REMEMBER
BARACK OBAMA IN 2007?
CORRECT ME IF I'M WRONG, DAVID,
BUT SORT OF SHUNNING THE IDEA
THAT WHITE PAPERS WERE NEEDED AS
HE WAS FIRST STARTING OUT HIS
CAMPAIGN ON EVERY POLICY?
>> YEAH, I ALSO REMEMBER, DAVID,
AND YOU WILL TOO, THAT HE
STUMBLED, HE WENT TO A TOWN HALL
IN LAS VEGAS ON HEALTH CARE.
>> YEAH.
>> AND DID VERY, VERY POORLY AND
THERE WERE A LOT OF PEOPLE WHO
WERE SAYING, YOU KNOW, MAYBE
HE'S NOT UP TO THIS.
MAYBE THE BEEF ISN'T THERE.
AND OVER THE COMING MONTHS HE
KIND OF LEVERAGED HIS WAY BACK
IN, THE DEBATES HELPED HIM DO
THAT.
SO WE SHOULD POINT OUT WE'RE AT
MILE TWO OF A 26-MILE MARATHON.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND SO PEOPLE WILL FALL
BEHIND AND CATCH UP, PEOPLE WILL
GO AHEAD AND FALL BEHIND.
BUT I DO THINK THAT BUTTIGIEG
HAS HAD A REMARKABLE RUN HERE.
BUT HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO --
HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO TURN THE
PAGE NOW AND GET TO THE NEXT
ACT.
>> LIKE ANY MARATHON NEVER
DISCOUNT THE LAST POINT TWO,
THAT'S WHEN WE KNOW.
AS WE'RE LOOKING AT THIS AND WE
NEED MORE -- WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
HOW WE NEED MORE SPECIFICS, YOU
BROUGHT THIS UP BRIEFLY AT THE
TOP OF THE HOUR, DAVID, BUT YOU
TWEETED EARLIER THAT KAMALA
HARRIS, I BELIEVE YOUR WORDS
WERE, LIKES TO STUDY STUFF
BECAUSE WE HEARD THAT FROM HER A
NUMBER OF TIMES.
WE PULLED A FEW OF THOSE
MOMENTS.
>> ELIZABETH WARREN IS HERE, AS
YOU KNOW, SHE SAID THAT SHE
SUPPORTS STUDENT LOAN
FORGIVENESS FOR 42 MILLION
AMERICANS.
>> YEAH.
>> WOULD YOU GO THAT FAR, DO YOU
SUPPORT THAT?
>> I SUPPORT ANYTHING THAT IS
ABOUT REDUCING THE DEBT OF
STUDENT LOANS, THAT'S AN
IMPORTANT CONVERSATION TO HAVE.
>> DO YOU SUPPORT FINANCIAL
REPARATIONS.
>> I SUPPORT THAT WE STUDY THAT.
>> DO YOU THINK AMERICANS HAVE
THE RIGHT TO VOTE AT AGE 16?
>> I'M INTERESTED IN HAVING THAT
CONVERSATION.
>> A LOT OF CONVERSATIONS AND
STUDYING HAPPENING.
>> SHE IS VERY CAUTIOUS AND
LAWYERLY AT TIMES.
SHE CAN BE SOARING AND
CHARISMATIC.
WHEN SHE GETS A QUESTION SHE'S
NOT SURE ABOUT SHE TENDS TO GO
TO THAT REFUGE.
AND THAT -- YOU KNOW, THE
THING -- I SAID A LONG TIME AGO
THAT PRESIDENTIAL RACES ARE MRIs
FOR THE SOUL.
LIKE, WHOEVER YOU ARE PEOPLE
KIND OF SCOPE THAT OUT AND THIS
WILL BECOME A NOTICED THING.
YOU HAVE TO COME AND YOU HAVE TO
BE READY TO ANSWER THESE
QUESTIONS HONESTLY AND OPENLY.
AND MAYBE THE ONTO ANSWER IS,
YOU KNOW, I HAVEN'T THOUGHT
ABOUT THAT.
>> RIGHT.
>> BUT --
>> IT WOULD SEEM MORE AND MORE,
AS PEOPLE BECOME MORE
TRANSPARENT THEY WANT THAT KIND
OF ANSWER.
>> I THINK THAT SORT OF A
AUTHENTICITY IS ABSOLUTELY
ESSENTIAL, ULTIMATELY, IF YOU'RE
GOING TO BE SUCCESSFUL IN A
PRESIDENTIAL RACE.
>> I THOUGHT HER ENERGY AND
PASSION TONIGHT REALLY SET HER
APART.
IN SOME WAYS I THINK A LOT OF
THE OTHER CANDIDATES, THERE WAS
A NERVOUSNESS, THERE WAS NOT
NECESSARILY CONNECTING WITH THE
AUDIENCE.
I THOUGHT WHEN SHE CAME OUT SHE
KIND OF BOUNDED ON STAGE,
CONNECTED WITH THE AUDIENCE,
TOLD SOME PERSONAL STORIES,
TALKED ABOUT HER OWN LIFE AND
HER OWN RECORD.
SO I THOUGHT SHE DID HERSELF
SOME REAL GOOD THERE.
I THINK I BEGAN TO SEE HER IN A
DIFFERENT LIGHT.
ONE OF THE, I THINK, RAPS ON HER
IS THAT SHE DIDN'T NECESSARILY
HAVE THE RETAIL POLITICAL SKILLS
A LOT OF OTHER FOLKS HAVE, SHE'S
BEEN ATTORNEY GENERAL, A
DIFFERENT THING THAN IF YOU'RE
MAYOR OR SENATOR.
YEAH, I THOUGHT IN THAT WAY
THERE WAS A WARMTH IN HER
TONIGHT.
>> SHE ALSO MADE A -- SHE MADE
NEWS TONIGHT BY SAYING SHE WOULD
ISSUE AN EXECUTIVE ORDER ON
GUNS.
>> SHE DID, YEAH.
>> IF CONGRESS DIDN'T ACT WITHIN
100 DAYS OF HER PRESIDENCY ON
BACKGROUND CHECKS.
SO THAT WAS -- THAT WAS CLEARLY
SOMETHING SHE PLANNED TO DO.
SHE CAME OUT AND SHE DID IT.
>> SPEAKING OF PLANNING, I'M
GOING TO GUESS THIS WAS PLANNED
BECAUSE THERE WAS A TOWN HALL.
I WAS GOING TO SAY, DAVID, IT
SETS US UP, SENATOR WARREN
RELEASING HER PROPOSAL TODAY TO
REALLY CANCEL OUT STUDENT DEBT.
YOU CAN SEE THE DETAILS THERE ON
THE SCREEN, BUT CANCELLING UP TO
$50,000 IN STUDENT LOAN DEBT
BASED ON INCOME FOR FOLKS MAKING
$100,000 OR LESS.
SHE ALSO TALKED VERY
SPECIFICALLY, THIS IS ALWAYS THE
QUESTION, OF COURSE, HOW DO YOU
PAY FOR IT?
HERE'S HER PLAN.
>> I STARTED IN SEVERAL MONTHS
AGO TALKING ABOUT A WEALTH TAX,
AN ULTRA MILLIONAIRE'S TAX, IT'S
TWO CENTS ON EVERY DOLLAR OF THE
GREAT FORTUNES ABOVE $50
MILLION.
SO YOUR 50 MILLIONTH AND FIRST
DOLLAR YOU'VE GOT TO PAY TWO
CENTS AND TWO CENTS ON ALL OF
THE DOLLARS AFTER THAT.
AND HERE'S THE STUNNING PART, IF
WE ASK THE GREAT FORTUNES IN
THIS COU AND UNDERSTAND THIS
ISN'T ABOUT TRYING TO BE NASTY
OR SAY THAT YOU'VE DONE ANYTHING
WRONG WHAT IT'S ABOUT IS SAYING,
LOOK YOU HAD A GREAT IDEA, YOU
GOT OUT THERE, YOU'VE WORKED
HARD OR YOU'VE INHERITED WELL,
WHICHEVER ONE IT WAS.
>> DAVID CHALIAN, ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT REALLY STUCK --
PARDON ME, STUCK OUT TO ME THERE
IS HER LANGUAGE.
IT'S NOT THAT SHE'S PREPARED AND
SHE'S GOT THIS, WE KNOW SHE
WANTS TO BE THE POLICY WONK HERE
IN THIS RACE, SHE'S SAYING TWO
CENTS, NOT 2%, WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT PENNIES, THIS IS VERY
CAREFULLY CHOSEN.
>> OH, WITHOUT A DOUBT.
AND, IN FACT, I THINK IF YOU
LOOK OVER TIME SHE HAS SHIFTED
TO THAT.
WHEN SHE FIRST ROLLED OUT THE
POLICY OF THE BIG WEALTH TAX
THAT SHE HAD PUT OUT THERE WAS,
YOU KNOW, 2% ON IN THE
OVER 50 MILLION RANGE AND THEN
3% ON BILLIONAIRES.
BUT NOW SHE'S INCORPORATING MUCH
MORE OF THIS NOTION OF PUTTING
THAT IN PERSPECTIVE FOR PEOPLE
AND USING, AS YOU SAID, WELL
CRAFTED LANGUAGE, SAYING WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT TWO CENTS ON THE
DOLLAR FOR THE DOLLARS OVER 50
MILLION.
SHE'S TRYING TO MAKE A POLICY
PROPOSAL MANY PEOPLE THINK WOULD
BE VERY HARD TO GET THROUGH
CONGRESS AND WOULD BE IN THE
CURRENT SET-UP, TRYING TO MAKE
IT MORE RELATABLE AND APPEALING
FOR PEOPLE AND THAT KIND OF
LANGUAGE CAN HELP FOR THAT.
I THINK ELIZABETH WARREN BY
COMING IN AND ROLLING OUT THAT
POLICY ON THIS DAY TO THIS CROWD
OF COLLEGE STUDENTS, THAT WAS NO
ACCIDENT.
AND THAT WAS PROBABLY A PRETTY
SHREWD POLITICAL MOVE FOR HER
TONIGHT BECAUSE IT'S A HUGELY
IMPORTANT ISSUE TO THESE FOLKS.
>> IT WAS EITHER A SHREWD MOVE
OR STUNNINGLY GOOD LUCK.
>> I'M GOING TO GO WITH SHREWD
AND WELL PLANNED.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT WAS REALLY
INTERESTING TO ME WAS BACK TO
BACK ELIZABETH WARREN AND BERNIE
SANDERS BECAUSE THEY'RE REALLY
IN MANY WAYS THEY'RE GOING AFTER
THE SAME VOTER.
THEY HAVE THE SAME OUTLOOK, THE
SAME SORT OF POPULIST OUTLOOK.
BUT SHE HAS COME IN WITH THIS
BATTERY OF VERY SPECIFIC
PROPOSALS.
SHE HAS PUT MEAT ON THE COLLEGE
FOR ALL PROPOSAL THAT SENATOR
SANDERS DEBUTED FOUR YEARS AGO
AND SO ON.
BUT THEY HAVE VERY DIFFERENT
STYLES AROUND THE SAME SET OF
ISSUES.
HE'S A LOT MORE RHETORICAL.
SHE'S MUCH MORE PROGRAM ATTIC.
>> IT IS FASCINATING TO WATCH.
STAY WITH US.
WE HAVE MUCH MORE TO DISCUSS,
INCLUDING WHO MAY HAVE BEST
CONNECTED WITH VOTERS TONIGHT.
WE TOUCHED ON IT A LITTLE BIT.
WHY IS IT SO IMPORTANT.
WHAT DOES IT SAY ABOUT THEIR
CHANCES FOR THE NOMINATION?
Uh-oh, looks like someone's
still nervous about buying
a new house.
Is it that obvious?
Yes it is.
You know, maybe you'd worry less
if you got GEICO to help with
your homeowners insurance.
I didn't know GEICO could helps
with homeowners insurance.
Yep,
they've been doing it for years.
What are you doing?
Big Steve?
Thanks, man.■@■@■@
Get to know GEICO and see
how much you could save on
homeowners and
renters insurance.
There's little rest
for a single dad,
and back pain made it hard to
sleep and get up on time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid,
plus the 12 hour pain
relieving strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a Better AM.
Whoooo.
Did you know the exact same
hotel room...
...can have many different
prices?
That's why TripAdvisor searches
over 200 booking sites
to find the lowest price on the
hotel you want.
Your perfect hotel room for the
perfect price!
Thanks to Priceline
working with top airlines
to turn their unsold seats
into amazing deals,
family reunion attendance is up.
We're all related!
Yeah, I see it.
And because Priceline
offers great deals
by comparing thousands
of prices in real time,
sports fans are seeing
more away games.
Various:
Yeah-h-h!
Is that safe?
Oh, y...
Ahh!
Not at all.
No, ma'am.
Nope.
And more people than ever are
enjoying romantic getaways.
(Romantic music)
That's gross
Priceline.
Every trip is a big deal.
That's gross
(ALARM BEEPING)
WELCOME TO OUR BUSY WORLD.
WHERE WE ALL WANT MORE ENERGY.
BUT WITH LESS CARBON FOOTPRINT.
THAT'S WHY, AT BP, WE'RE
WORKING TO MAKE ENERGY
THAT'S CLEANER AND BETTER.
WE'RE PRODUCING
CLEANER-BURNING NATURAL GAS.
AND SOLAR AND WIND POWER.
AND WHEREVER YOUR
DAY TAKES YOU...
WE HAVE ADVANCED FUELS
FOR A BETTER COMMUTE.
AND WE'RE DEVELOPING
ULTRA-FAST-CHARGING
TECHNOLOGY FOR EVs..
AT BP, WE SEE
POSSIBILITIES EVERYWHERE.
SO WE CAN ALL KEEP ADVANCING.
>>> FIVE DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIA
CANDIDATES SPEAKING DIRECTLY TO
VOTERS, TONIGHT IN THE AUDIENCE
COLLEGE-AGE VOTERS, STUDENTS
ASKING THOSE QUESTIONS.
SO WHO WAS ABLE TO BEST
aaaT■TESSAGE?
DAVID CHALIAN, NIA-MALIKA
HENDERSON AND DAVID AXELROD BACK
WITH US.
AS WE LISTEN TO DIFFERENT
MOMENTS, THERE'S BEEN A LOT SAID
AND A LOT MADE OF WHAT WE'VE
BEEN HEARING IN RECENT WEEKS
FROM PETE BUTTIGIEG IN RELATION
TO MIKE PENCE.
>> YOU GOT INTO A PUBLIC BACK
AND FORTH BETWEEN VICE PRESIDENT
PENCE AND YOURSELF OVER
DISCRIMINATIONS OVER LGBTQ
PEOPLE AND FAITH.
RICHARD GRE NELL WEIGHED IN ON
THIS SAYING YOU'VE BEEN "PUSHING
THIS HATE HOAX ALONG THE LINES
OF JUSSIE SMOLLETT LONG TIME --
>> I KNOW BAIT WHEN I SEE IT AND
I'M NOT GOING TO TAKE IT.
>> ALL RIGHT, OUR NEXT
QUESTION --
>> HE WASN'T TAKING IT.
DAVID CHALIAN, HOW DID THAT GO
OVER THERE IN THE HALL?
>> IT WAS ONE OF THE BIGGEST
CROWD PLEASING LINES OF THE
NIGHT FOR THIS AUDIENCE AND I
THINK, YOU KNOW, WHAT THAT SHOWS
RIGHT THERE, RIGHT, THAT IS PART
OF WHY, AS DAVID AXELROD WAS
DESCRIBING BUTTIGIEG HAS HAD
THESE ROCKET BOOSTERS ON BECAUSE
THAT'S RAW POLITICAL SKILL RIGHT
THERE TO HAVE RICK GRENELL
TROLLING HIM ANDsTsT■T■T■TUSAL
GET REENGAGED IN A WAY WITH
SOMEBODY WHO'S NOT VICE
PRESIDENT PENCE MAKES LITTLE
SENSE TO HIM AND HE WAS ABLE TO
DISPATCH WITH THAT PRETTY
QUICKLY.
I WILL SAY, THOUGH, THE LARGER
BATTLE THAT WE SAWsTsTsTsTsTsT
HAVING WITH PENCE, YOU KNOW, I
THINK LY POLITICALLY
FORENCE AND BUTTIGIEG.
AND I THINK THEY BOTH REALIZE
THAT SO THEY SORT OF SEEM TO BE
OVER THE COURSE OF THEIR BACK
AND FORTH I THOUGHT A REAL
UNDERSTANDING THAT IT WAS
WORKING FOR EACH OF THEIR
POLITICAL NEEDS.
>> IT'S NOT GOING ANYWHERE
ANYTIME SOON IS WHAT I'M ALSO
READING BETWEEN THE LINES THERE
FROM YOU.
AS WE'RE LOOKING AT THE WAY
PEOPLE WERE CONNECTING, AMY
KLOBUCHAR WAS UP FIRST, THE
SENATOR SEEMED A LITTLE NERVOUS,
I WILL SAY IN THE BEGINNING,
CLEARLY TRYING TO CONNECT WITH
HER AUDIENCE, NOT ALL OF THOSE
MOMENTS SEEMED TO WORK.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> I AM SOMEONE THAT RUNS IN A
PURPLE STATE.
IT IS A STATE THAT WHEN I FIRST
STARTED RUNNING FOR OFFICE THE
OTHER SENATOR WAS REPUBLICAN,
THE GOVERNOR WAS REPUBLICAN AND
THREE OF OUR FOUR CONSTITUTIONAL
OFFERS WERE REPUBLICAN.
AND THEN I STARTED RUNNING.
AND EVERY SINGLE TIME I HAVE RUN
I HAVE WON EVERY SINGLE
CONGRESSIONAL DISTRICT IN MY
STATE, INCLUDING MICHELLE
BOOKMAN'S, OKAY, THAT'S WHEN YOU
GUYS ARE SUPPOSED TO CHEER.
SO I --
>> THAT IS A GOOD MOMENT, RIGHT,
FOR HER TO LAY IT OUT LIKE THAT
AND SAYING I AM THE PERSON WHO
CAN WIN IN ALL OF THESE PLACES
BUT YOU DON'T WANT TO TELL
PEOPLE TO CHEER, DAVID.
>> THAT WAS THE JEB BUSH MOMENT,
REMEMBER THAT, WHEN HE SAID YOU
CAN CLAP NOW.
THAT WAS NOT A GOOD MOMENT.
BUT ON THE WHOLE THAT WAS A
STRONG ANSWER FOR HER AND SHE
DID SHOW FLASHES OF HUMOR, ONE
OF WHICH WAS AT THE EXPENSE OF
OUR COLLEAGUE CHRIS CUOMO WHEN
HE WAS TRYING TO GET HER TO
FINISH AN ANSWER.
SO THAT WAS TO HER BENEFIT.
SHE'S A MODERATE AND SHE'S
SELLING HERSELF AS A MODERATE
AND SHE'S TALKING TO AN AUDIENCE
THERE OF YOUNG PEOPLE, THE
HARVARD POLL SAID THAT 80% OF
THEM SAID THEY'D RATHER BE WITH
SOMEONE WHO REFLECTS THEIR
POINTS OF VIEW THAN SOMEONE WHO
ARGUES THEY CAN BEAT THE
PRESIDENT.
THIS WASN'T NECESSARILY HER
CROWD, SHE WAS REALLY SPEAKING
TO THE BROADER AUDIENCE OUT
THERE.
HER ARGUMENT IS I'M A MIDWESTERN
CENTER LEFT POLITICIAN WHO HAS A
BETTER CHANCE OF WINNING THOSE
STATES THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
CARRIED TO WIN THE PRESIDENCY IN
2016.
>> AND YOU SAW THAT IN HER
ANSWERS IN THE IMPEACHMENT
ANSWER BASICALLY SHE'S ON THE
SENATE SIDE LET THE HOUSE TAKE
CARE OF THAT IN TERMS OF WHETHER
OR NOT THEY WANT TO FILE
ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT AND YOU
SAW THAT IN TERMS OF HER ANSWER
ABOUT COLLEGE AND SHE SAID AT
ONE POINT LISTEN I CAN'T STAPLE
A COLLEGE DIPLOMA ONTO THE
BOTTOM OF YOUR SEATS, AN
IMPRACTICAL IDEA THAT YOU CAN
FORGIVE STUDENT LOAN DEBT, MAKE
COLLEGE FREE, PUBLIC COLLEGES
FREE.
>> AND THAT'S GOT APPEAL TOO,
ROOTED IN THE MIDWESTERN, YOU
KNOW, IT'S NOT JUST --
>> HARD WORK AND ALL THAT STUFF.
>> IT'S ABOUT LET'S BE HONEST
WITH WHERE WE STAND RIGHT HERE.
WE CAN'T AFFORD THAT, WE'RE NOT
DOING IT.
HEY, I'D LOVE TO, BUT THERE'S
SOMETHING TO BE SAID FOR THAT.
>> IT'S THAT MIDWESTERN
PRACTICALITY THAT SHE'S RUNNING
ON.
THESE HARVARD STUDENTS ARE MORE
LIKELY WITH FOLKS LIKE BERNIE,
IF YOU LOOK AT EARLY POLLS OUT
OF THE HARVARD INSTITUTE OF THE
IOP A LOT OF THEM ARE WITH
BERNIE AT THIS POINT.
>> SHE COULD HAVE GOTTEN MORE
OUT OF THAT MOMENT IF SHE HAD
BEEN EVEN MORE DIRECT RIGHT FROM
THE START OF THAT ANSWER ABOUT
ELIZABETH WARREN SAYING NO, I
DON'T AGREE WITH THAT AND THIS
IS WHY.
AND SHE SORT OF DANCED AROUND IT
A LITTLE BIT AND SHE TRIED TO BE
THE TRUTH TELLER.
TRIED TO PUT THE PILL IN THE
APPLESAUCE SORT OF.
AND THAT'S NOT -- YOU EITHER
HAVE TO BE THE TRUTH TELLER OR
NOT.
>> LISTENING TO ALL OF THIS, I
FOUND IT INTERESTING SENATOR
WARREN WAS ASKED WHAT SHE
LEARNED FROM HILLARY CLINTON IN
2016.
AND CONCERNS ABOUT SEXISM AND
HER ANSWER ACTUALLY WENT BACK A
LITTLE BIT FURTHER AND MAY HAVE
SURPRISED A FAIR AMOUNT OF
PEOPLE.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> SO EVERY DAY WHEN I SAW A
LITTLE GIRL I WOULD COME UP AND
I'D USUALLY GET DOWN, I'M A
TEACHER, AND I WOULD SAY HI, MY
NAME IS ELIZABETH.
AND I'M RUNNING FOR SENATE.
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT GIRLS DO.
AND THEN WE WOULD PINKY SWEAR TO
REMEMBER.
AND SO EVERY NIGHT WHEN I WENT
HOME NO MATTER WHAT THE DAY HAD
BEEN LIKE I WOULD COUNT UP HOW
MANY PINKY SWEARS WE'D DONE
DURING THE DAY.
>> DAVID CHALIAN,THATaakkk
PLAYING?
>> YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT IT WAS A
QUITE FRANKLY I THINK ELIZABETH
WARREN HAD A R STR
AS A STORY TELLER AND
PERFORMER I THINK WHEN YOU LOOK
AT THE FIELD ACROSS THE
THEM CAMPAIGNING ON  TRAIL RIGF
THE MOST CONSISTENT PERFORMERS
ON THAT SCORE.
I WILL TELL YOU HER CAMPAIGN
THOUGHT SO MUCH OF THAT MOMENT
THAT THAT'S WHAT THEY CLIPPED
AND SENT OUT TO THEIR
SUPPORTERS.
THEY'RE HOPING THAT BRINGS IN
SOME DOLLARS, BRINGS IN SOME
EMAIL ADDRESSES AND ORGANIZING
EFFORT BECAUSE WHAT YOU DIDN'T
SEE ELIZABETH WARREN DO THERE,
WHICH I THOUGHT WAS INTERESTING
IN HOW SHE ANSWET
QUESTION, ERICA, WAS SHE DID NOT
TOUCH THE HILLARY CLINTON
OF THAT AT ALL.
THE QUESTION WAS, ARE YOU GOING
TO BE HILLARIED?
AND SHE JUST WENT INTO AN
ENTIRELY DIFFERENT DIRECTION,
DID NOT SEEM TO WANT TO SORT OF
ASSOCIATE HERSELF WITH HILLARY
CLINTON OR IN ANY WAY RELITIGATE
2016 BUT INSTEAD WANTED TO TELL
WHAT SHE THINKS IS AN
INSPIRATIONAL STORY FROM HER
LIFE ON THE TRAIL AND IT'S ONE
HER CAMPAIGN CLEARLY THINKS CAN
GIVE THEM A BIT OF AN ADVANTAGE.
>> AN ASIDE ON THIS, BUT SHE
TALKED ABOUT BEING A TEACHER,
YOU KNOW I WAS A TEACHER AND SHE
TALKED EARLIER ABOUT HAVING
STUDIED TO BECOME A SPECIAL
NEEDS TEACHER WHICH SHE DID
BRIEFLY IN HER LIFE AND ALL
THROUGHOUT SHE WAS REFERRING TO
HERSELF AS A TEACHER BUT SHE
NEVER MENTIONED THE LAST 30
YEARS OR SO SHE'S SPENT TEACHING
AT HARVARD UNIVERSITY IN A ROOM
FULL OF HARVARD STUDENTS.
THERE'S A REASON FOR THAT AS
WELL.
THAT, I DON'T THINK THEY FEEL IS
A CREDENTIAL THEY WANT TO
BURNISH OUT THERE.
SHE'S TRYING TO BE A TRIBUNE OF
EVERYDAY PEOPLE AND THAT'S A
KIND OF SEPARATION THAT SHE
DOESN'T WANT TO ACCENTUATE.
>> IT'S A MARKER OF ELITISM.
SHE WAS AT HARVARD -- EVEN
THOUGH SHE WAS THERE IN FRONT OF
A LOT OF HARVARD KIDS IT WASN'T
A CARD SHE WANTED TO PLAY
BECAUSE, AGAIN, SHE LIKES TO
TALK ABOUT HER HARD SCRABBLE
ROOTS IN OKLAHOMA.
>> ALL LEGITIMATE.
>> IT'S ALL LEGITIMATE AND SHE
TELLS IT VERY EFFECTIVELY.
YOU'VE SEEN HER OUT ON THE
STUMP, PEOPLE REALLY CONNECT
WITH THE STORIES SHE TELLS ABOUT
GROWING UP AND DROPPING OUT OF
COLLEGE, AND HER FIRST MARRIAGE
WENT BAD AND ALL THOSE KINDS OF
STORIES.
>> HER BIOGRAPHY IS FOUNDATIONAL
FOR HER POLITICS AND THERE'S NO
QUESTION ABOUT IT.
DAVID SAYS SHE'S A GREAT STORY
TELLER.
MY QUESTION IS, IS SHE TOO GOOD
A STORY TELLER?
EVERY ANSWER FEELS LIKE A TED
TALK TO ME, AND IS IT TOO
POLISHED?
IS IT TOO PRACTICED?
DOES IT SEEM TOO MUCH LIKE A
PERFORMANCE AND NOT AN ANSWER?
I DON'T KNOW THE QUESTION -- I
DON'T KNOW THE ANSWER TO THAT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, SHE'S HAD SOME
PROBLEMS CONNECTING, MAYBE NOT
IN THE ROOM, BUT CERTAINLY
BROADLY TO THIS POINT AND I
WONDER IF THAT'S A BARRIER
BECAUSE THE POLICY IS THERE, THE
BIOGRAPHY IS THERE, ALL THE IND
GREEDIENTS SHOULD BE THERE FOR
HER TO DO VERY WELL.
>> THIS IN SOME WAYS RELATES TO
THE QUESTION OF GENDER, RIGHT,
CAN A WOMAN ACTUALLY
BREAKTHROUGH?
IF YOU LOOK AT ALL OF THE POLLS,
AND LET'S BE HONEST IT'S EARLY,
I MEAN THE FOLKS WHO ARE LEADING
THE POLLS, BIDEN, BERNIE
SANDERS, THERE WAS A POLL OUT OF
NEW HAMPSHIRE MORE RECENTLY, A
SMALL STAMP SIZE, BUT I THINK
MAYOR PETE WAS DOING PRETTY WELL
IN THIS POLL, THERE IS THIS
CONVERSATION GOING ON AMONG
DEMOCRATS, AMONG -- DEMOCRATS OF
ALL STRIPES, AFRICAN-AMERICANS,
LATINOS, WHITE VOTERS AS WELL,
CAN A WOMAN ACTUALLY WIN?
AFTER THE HEARTBREAK THAT MANY
DEMOCRATS EXPERIENCED IN 2016
MAYBE THEY WANT TO GO WITH A
SAFER CHOICE THIS GO ROUND AND
THE SAFER CHOICE LOOKS MORE LIKE
BIDEN AND MORE LIKE SOMEBODY
LIKE BERNIE SANDERS, A WHITE
MALE.
>> WITH ALL OF THESE DEMOCRATS,
OF COURSE, VYING FOR THE WHITE
HOUSE, THEY'RE FACING A CRITICAL
QUESTION OF WHO CAN ACTUALLY
BEAT PRESIDENT TRUMP, IS IT A
WOMAN, IS IT A WHITE MAN?
WE'LL DISSECT NEXT.
After walking six miles at
an amusement park...
Bill's back needed a
vacation from his vacation.
So he stepped on the
Dr. Scholl's kiosk.
It recommends our best
Custom Fit Orthotic
to relieve foot, knee, or
lower back pain.
So you can move more.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to move.
Everyone's got to listen to mom.
When it comes to reducing the
sugar in your family's diet,
Coke, Dr Pepper and Pepsi hear
you.
We're working together to do
just that.■p■p■p■p■p.
Smaller portion sizes,
clear calorie labels and
reminders to think balance.
Because we know mom wants what's
best.
More beverage choices, smaller
portions, less sugar.
BalanceUS.org
-Omar, look.
Omar, check this out.
Uh, yeah, I was calling to see
if you do laser hair removal.
For men.
Notice that my hips
are off the ground.
[ Engine revving ]
And then, I'm gonna pike
my hips back into downward dog.
[ Rhythmic tapping ]
Hey, the rain stopped.
-A bad day on the road
still beats a good one off it.
-Tell me about
that dental procedure again!
-I can still
taste it in my mouth!
-Progressive
helps keep you out there.
There are people out there
-I can still
taste it in my mouth!
who see things others can't.
They're the ones
who see a city
that can make
those who live in it
feel a little safer.
Who see cars that can
talk to each other
and share their best shortcuts.
Who see the efficient shape and
design of the ocean's wonders
as the future of aerodynamics.
♪  ♪■@■ ■@
they can see the
infinite possibilities@@
of the power of data
flowing through our world.
At Dell Technologies,
we see it too.
And we can help make
your digital future real
so you can move the world
forward in beautif■■,
unimaginable ways.
If you'd like to transform
your business, talk to us.
And together we'll
show the world
what impossible looks like...
when it's made real.
>>> THE FIVE CANDIDATES YOU
HEARD FROM TONIGHT HAVE THE SAME
GOAL, THEY WANT TO BEAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP IN 2020.
BACK AND DAVID CHALIAN,
NIA-MALIKA HENDERSON AND DAVID
AXELROD.
LOOKING AT THE POLLING, BERNIE
SANDERS IS CONSISTENTLY AT THE
TOP AND HE WAS ASKED
SPECIFICALLY TONIGHT WHY IS IT
HE THINKS THAT YOUNG VOTERS ARE
REALLY STILL LOOKING TO BERNIE
SANDERS.
HERE'S HIS ANSWER.
>> YOUR GENERATION, UNLESS WE
TURN THINGS AROUND, WILL BE THE
FIRST GENERATION IN THE MODERN
HISTORY OF AMERICA TO HAVE A
LOWER STANDARD OF LIVING THAN
YOUR PARENTS.
WE HAVE SEEN AN EXPLOSION IN
WORKER PRODUCTIVITY BUT
EVERYTHING BEING EQUAL MANY
PEOPLE IN YOUR GENERATION WILL
EARN LESS MONEY THAN YOUR
PARENTS, YOU'RE GOING TO LEAVE
SCHOOL MORE DEEPLY IN DEBT THAN
YOUR PARENTS, YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE A HARDER TIME FINDING
AFFORDABLE HOUSING THAN YOUR
PARENTS.
I THINK THOSE ARE SOME OF THE
REASONS WHY OUR MESSAGE HAS
RESONATED WITH YOUNG PEOPLE.
EARLIER THaLaLIGHT ON HERE N
DAVID CHALIAN, A LOT OF WHAT WE
TALKED ABOUT WHEN WE LOOKED AT
POLLING WAS ALSO NAME
RECOGNITION.
THE FACT THAT BERNIE SANDERS IS
WELL-KNOWN AMONG YOUNG VOTERS
AND THEaL SUPPORT HE HAD IN 201.
IS THIS ABOUT NAME RECOGNITION
OR THE FACT THAT THEY BELIEVE HE
IDENTIFIES WITH THEIR POLICY AND
HIS VISION?
DAVID CHALIAN.
>> IT'S A OF BOTH/AND KIND OF
THING.
IT'S A BIT OF BOTH, ERICA.
I DON'T WANT TO DIMINISH BERNIE
SANDERS SUPPORT AND SAY HE'S
ONLY RIDING HIGH IN THE POLLS
BECAUSE OF NAME RECOGNITION.
HE FORMED A REAL BASE OF SUPPORT
AND THERE IS A BIG CHUNK OF THAT
SUPPORT THAT IS SHOWING BACK UP
FOR HIM AGAIN THIS CYCLE, GOING
TO WHAT DAVID AXELROD WAS SAYING
ABOUT -- HE SEEMS TO HAVE A HOLD
ON THEM WHICH IS MAKING IT, I
THINK, DIFFICULT FOR HER TO GET
A FOOTHOLD AND MAKE REAL
TRACTION.
SO IT IS PARTIALLY THAT HE IS
CERTAINLY, OF ALL THE PEOPLE ON
THE STAGE, ONE OF THE BEST KNOWN
IF NOT THE BEST KNOWN.
BUT ALSO, AS YOU NOTED, THIS WAS
PART OF HIS CO LALITION, THE YOH
N 2016 AGAINST HILLARY
CLINTON, HE WON THOSE
MILLENNIALS AND HE HAS BEEN ABLE
TO KEEP THAT CONVERSATION GOING
WITH THEM OVER THE COURSEkk OF E
LAST FOUR YEARS, AND MANY OF
THEM ARE STILL FINDING HIM AN
APPEALING CHOICE AT THIS STAGE
OF THE GAME.
>> IT'S KIND OF PARADOXICAL.
HE'S 79 YEARS OLD AND HE IS
FAVORED BY SO MANY YOUNG PEOPLE.
AND PART OF IT IS THAT HE SPEAKS
IN -- HE IS NOT AN
INCREMENTALIST.
FOR THOSE IMPATIENT FOR
SOLUTIONS HE DOES NOT SPEAK IN
INCREMENTAL SOLUTIONS.
HE TALKS ABOUT BIG BOLD
STRUCTURAL REFORMS.
BUT I'LL SAY, YOU KNOW, LAST
TIME HE HAD THE FIELD TO HIMSELF
IT WAS -- IT WAS BERNIE SANDERS
VERSUS HILLARY CLINTON.
NOW NOT JUST ELIZABETH WARREN
BUT COMPETING FOR THESE YOUNGER
VOTERS YOU HAVE KAMALA HARRIS,
YOU HAVE PETE BUTTIGIEG, YOU
HAVE BETO O'ROURKE.
HE'S
IF I WERE HIM THAT THIS WAS THIS
IS HIS SOLID AND BASE.
>> SOMETHING ELSE THAT STOOD
OUT.
KAMALA HARRIS ASKED ABOUT HER
COMMENT ABOUT WINNING BACK
MIDWEST VOTERS.
>> THE CONVERSATION THAT ALL OF
US HAVE BEEN HEARING.
ESPECIALLY THE 2020 ELECTION.
WHICH IS A CONVERSATION SAYING
WHO CAN TALK TO THE PERSON IN
THE MIDWEST.
I JUST REJECT THAT NOTION.
THAT YOU HAVE ONE CONVERSATION
WITH SOMEONE IN THE MIDWEST AND
ANOTHER CONVERSATION WITH
SOMEBODY IN THE SOUTH AND
ANOTHER CONVERSATION ON THE
COAST.
I REJECT THAT NOTION.
IT IS SHORT SIDED, AND IT IS
ACTUALLY NOT CONNECTED WITH
WHERE PEOPLE REALLY ARE.
THE AMERICAN PUBLIC DON'T WANT
THAT.
THEY DON'T WANT THAT.
>> THIS IS A VERSION OF OBAMA'S
LINE ABOUT THERE'S NO RED
AMERICA OR BLUE AMERICA.
THERE'S THE UNITED STATES OF
AMERICA.
WHICH GOT HUGE APPLAUSE WHEN HE
DELIVERED THIS LINE.
IN 2004.
CLEARLY WHAT SHE'S TALKING ABOUT
WITHOUT REALLY SAYING IT, THE
IDEA IS CAN SHE APPEAL TO VOTERS
IN THE MIDWEST WHO ARE WHITE.
RIGHT?
CAN A BLACK WOMAN WHO IS FROM
CALIFORNIA WHO HAS A CERTAIN
RECORD OF PROGRESSIVE RECORD OUT
THERE CAN SHE APPEAL TO THE
WORKING CLASS WHITE GUY WHO
WORKS IN A FACTORY.
OR A WAITRESS.
OR WHITE WOMAN WRATSZ OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
OR APPEAL TO BLACK VOTERS IN THE
SOUTH.
WE DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S THE CONVERSATION THAT
EVERYBODY IS HAVING.
DOES IT TAKE A WHITE MAN TO
APPEAL TO THOSE VOTERS OR CAN
SHE DO IT THE WAY OBAMA DID.
HE PUT TOGETHER A BROAD
COALITION.
>> HE WAS FROM ILLINOIS.
THE STATE NEXT TO IOWA.
WHICH MADE IT EASY FOR HIM.
THE OTHER WAY THERE'S NO DOUBT
THAT THERE ARE MANY PEOPLE IN
THE COUNTRY AND DEMOCRATS WHO
ARE TIRED OF BEING DIVIDED.
FEEL THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN A
DEVICIVE FORCE.
SHE WAS SPEAKING TO THEM.
IT WOULD BE READ AS A REBUKE FOR
EXAMPLE THE SENATOR KLOBUCHAR
WHO MADE A PRONOUNCED EFFORT AT
THIS TOWN HALL TO SAY I'M THE
ONE WHO CAN WIN THE MIDWEST
VOTERS IN A SENSE WHAT SENATOR
HARRIS IS SAYING THAT'S THE
WRONG WAY TO GO.
>> THIS STOOD OUT TO YOU.
SO SENATOR WARREN WAS ASKED WHY
SHE SHIFTED FROM BEING
REPUBLICAN TO DEMOCRAT.
SHE TALKED ABOUT HER EXPERIENCE
WORKING ON BANKRUPTCY AND HERE'S
HOW SHE LAID IT OUT.
>> BY THE END OF THAT FIGHT I
PULLY UNDERSTOOD THAT EVERY
SINGLE REPUBLICAN STOOD THERE
FROM THE BANK AND HALF OF THE
DEMOCRATS DID.
SO MY PARTY WAS THE PARTY THAT
HAT LEAST WE GOT HALF OF THEM TO
STAND UP FOR WORKING PEOPLE.
THAT WAS A BIG CHANGE FOR ME.
>> BANKRUPTCY BILL OF 2005.
WHICH REALLY ADVANTAGED CREDIT
CARD COMPANIES AND ONE OF THE
PROMOENT POENTS OF THAT
LEGISLATION WAS JOE WIDEN.
SENATOR IN DELAWARE.
WHERE THE COMPANIES ARE MANY OF
THEM ARE HEADQUARTERED.
I EXPECT THIS WAS A SHOT ACROSS
THE BOW AT THE VICE PRESIDENT.
WHO WERE TOLD IS GOING IT ENTER
THE RACE.
IT'S SOMETHING WE CAN EXPECT TO
HEAR FROM SENATOR WARREN AS WE
MOVE ALONG.
>> IT'S FASCINATING TO WATCH
THAT.
JUST THE SHEER VOLUME OF WHAT WE
SAW TONIGHT.
THE FACT THAT EACH ONE OF THE
ATESNG BACKOCK.
WHAT WAS FASCINATING IS WATCH
EACH ONE PICK UP WHAT HAD COME
BEFORE.
NOT JUST IN THE QUESTIONING BUT
IN THE WAY THEY SEEM TO BEc
REACTING TO THE ANSWERS THAT
CAME BAEFORE AND THE AUDIENCE.
>> IT WAS THE FIRST OPPORTUNITY
OF THIS CYCLE SO FAR.
AND AGAIN WE ARE IN THE EARLY
STAGES.
TO START SIZING THEM UP AGAINST
EACH OTHER.
THIS IS WHY THE POINTS THAT
DAVID WERE MAKING BEFORE ABOUT
KAMALA HARRIS'S CAUTION AND
WHETHER OR NOT IT'S A LIABILITY.
IN A SLOW LOW EVENT THAT MAY NOT
HAVE BEEN QUITE AS GLARING AS ON
A NIGHT WHEN THERE ARE SEVERAL
COMPETITORS WHO WERE ANSWERING
MUCH MANY DIRECTLY ON SOME
QUESTIONS.
YOU ALL OF A SUDDEN ARE STARTING
TO SEE THIS NEXT PHASE OF THIS
CAMPAIGN.
WHERE THESE FOLKS ARE GOING FOB
SIZED UP AGAINST EACH OTHER.
HERE IT WAS IN SUCCESSION ON
THIS SAME STAGE BEFORE THE SAME
AUDIENCE.
WE'RE ONLY A FEW WEEKS AWAY FROM
THE FIRST DEBATE WHERE THEY WILL
BE ON THE STAGE TOGETHER.
AND REALLY MIXING IT UP.
I THINK THIS AFFORDED US A NEW
OPPORTUNITY AND NEW LENS TO
WHICH WE CAN START ASSESSING
CANDIDATES.
>> IT WAS GREAT TO WATCH.
AND ALWAYS FUN TO TALK ABOUT IT
ALL WITH THE THREE OF YOU.
THANK YOU.
THANKS TO YOU AT HOME FOR
WATCHING.
OUR LIVE COVERAGE CONTINUES
RIGHT AFTER THIS.
Up.
Down.
Ah ah!
That's one.
Up.
That's two.
Down.
Get down,
get down.
Feel the clarity of
non-drowsy Claritin
and relief from
Symptoms caused
by over
200 indoor
and outdoor
allergens.
Like those
from buddy.
Because stuffed
animals
are clearly no subfor re.
Feel the clarity.
And Live Claritin clear.
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now at T-Mobile buy any
Samsung Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e Free!
♪ ♪
Plants capture CO2.
What if other kinds of plants
captured it too?■■C
If these industrial plants had
tech■■çs■g■g■g■O■O■@s
we could help lower emissions.
Carbon Capture is important
technology -
and experts agree.
That's why we're working on ways
to improve it.
So plants...
can be a little more...
like plants.
♪ ♪
Whoooo.
Did you know the exact same
hotel room...
...can have many different
prices?
That's why TripAdvisor searches
over 200 booking sites
to find the lowest price on the
hotel you want.
Your perfect hotel room for the
perfect price!
Cooper!
Did you eat all of your treats?
♪ Help! I need somebody
♪ Help! Not just anybody
♪ Help! You know I need someone
Here you go little guy.
A cockroach can
survive submerged
underwater for 30 minutes.
Wow.
Yeah, wow.
■8
Not getting in today.
Not on my watch.
Pests never stop
trying to get in.
We never stop working
to keep them out.
Terminix. Defenders of Home.
>>> HELLO, WELCOME TO OUR
VIEWERS IN THE UNITED STATES AND
AROUND THE WORLD.
AMIDFEAR OF ATTACKS OFFICIALS IN
SRI LANKA DECLARE A AN
EMERGENCY.