>>> THIS IS "DAILY BLAST LIVE."
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>> EVERYBODY IS TALKING ABOUT
THIS.
>> ALWAYS LIVE, ALWAYS REAL,
ALWAYS UNPREDICTABLE.
>> YOU ARE TOTALLY OFF BASE
HERE.
>> LOG ON AND JOIN OUR LIVE
CONVERSATION.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M SAYING
THIS.
I DO AGREE WITH YOU.
>> "DBL" STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> THREE, TWO --
>> WELCOME TO "DBL."
IT'S TUESDAY, FEBRUARY 19th.
WE ARE LIVE AND WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT.
LET'S GET STARTED.
WE BEGIN WITH BIG NEWS FOR
BERNIE SANDERS FANS.
THE SENATOR ANNOUNCED HE IS
RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT.
HERE IS WITH HE TOLD CBS NEWS.
>> SO SENATOR SANDERS, YOU'RE
GOING TO RUN FOR PRESIDENT.
>> I'M GOING TO RUN FOR
PRESIDENT.
>> WHAT'S GOING TO BE DIFFERENT
THIS TIME?
WE'RE GOING TO WIN.
>> HE LOST TO HILLARY CLINTON
IN THE 2016 DEMOCRATIC PRIMARY.
NOW HE IS BACK RUNNING ON HIS
SIGNATURE POLICY.
THIS IS WHAT HE TWEETED.
>> IF WE ARE PREPARED TO STAND
TOGETHER, THAT IS NO END TO
WHAT THE GREAT PEOPLE OF OUR
NATION CAN ACCOMPLISH.
>> AND BERNIE IS JOINING A VERY
CROWDED FIELD OF DEMOCRATIC
CANDIDATES INCLUDING CORY
BOOKER, SENATOR AMY KLOBUCHAR,
HARRIS AND MANY MORE.
THAT'S ONLY ONE OTHER
REPUBLICAN CHALLENGING HIM,
BILL WELD.
SO, TORY, WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING
FOR AS A CANDIDATE?
INTO DO I WANT TO SAY POLICY,
GUN VIOLENCE AND CLIMATE
CHANGE, YES.
SOMEONE WHO CAN SPEAK TO TRUMP
IN A WAY THAT I FEEL
COMFORTABLE KNOWING THEY ARE
THE ADULT IN THE ROOM.
>> SO YOU WANT CIVIL POLITICS.
>> I WANT A LEADER.
I NEED SOMEONE WHO SPEAKS AND
ACTS LIKE A LEADER AND TO
RECOGNIZE THE RUST BELT,
MINNESOTA, WISCONSIN NEEDS TO
BE LOOKED AT AND HILLARY
CLINTON LOST THAT.
KLOBUCHAR IS SAYING I'M GOING
TO THE PLACES SHE DIDN'T GO.
I'M LOOKING AT KAMALA.
MANY ARE SAYING HE DOESN'T HAVE
THE MOMENTUM.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO I'M GOING
TO VOTE FOR IN 2020.
I WANT TO SEE ALL THE
CANDIDATES, ALL THE DEBATES.
I DO WANT TO SEE MONEY OUT OF
POLITICS AND THERE'S ONE PERSON
I CAN THINK OF IS BERNIE
SANDERS.
HIS POLITICS HAVE ALWAYS
SUPPORTED THAT.
WHAT DO YOU HOPE TO SEE IN
KIDNAPPED IN 2020, ERICA.
>> GOSH, IT'S ONE OF THOSE
THINGS I WILL KNOW IT WHEN I
SEE IT.
YOU HAVE TO VOTE YOUR CONSCIOUS
AND WHAT PAYS YOUR BILLS.
I CAN UNDERSTAND PEOPLE EVEN IN
THEIR LIVELIHOODS ARE
CONSIDERED ANTIQUATED, THEY ARE
GOING TO VOTE FOR THE PERSON
WHO GIVES ME THE PROMISE.
THIS WAS OIL AND GAS THAT LOST
ME WITH BERNIE SANDERS.
OIL AND GAS FEEDS MY FAMILY.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU?
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT TO SEE IN
2020?
>> I WANT TO SEE MORE PEOPLE TO
HAVE THE COURAGE THAT YOU SAY,
I DON'T KNOW.
I WILL MAKE A DECISION AFTER I
THOROUGHLY VETTED EACH
CANDIDATE.
FREE COLLEGE.
THAT'S NOT A BLUEPRINT FOR A
SUCCESSFUL COUNTRY.
FIGURE OUT WHAT'S GOING TO WORK
BEST FOR YOU AND YOUR COMMUNITY
AND GO BASED OFF THAT.
>> I WILL SAY TRUMP'S NAGS
SPOKESPERSON SAID BERNIE WON
BECAUSE HIS IDEAS ARE WHAT
EVERYBODIES ARE AND HE IS THE
OG AND HE HAD THOSE MANY YEARS.
>> WE WANT TO HEAR FROM YOU DBL
NATION.
WE WANT IT HEAR FROM YOU.
>>> WELL, THE WORLD BOXER ONE
OF THE MOST ICONIC FASHION
DESIGNERS, KARL LAGERFELD.
HE WAS THE CREATIVE DIRECTOR OF
CHANNEL AND TENDI.
HE DRESSED ALMOST ALL OF THE
FAMOUS WINTER OF OUR TIME
INCLUDING ANNA WINTORP, MARIAH
CARRY, BEYONCE.
AND THIS WORN BY PRINCESS DIANE
NA.
NAOMI CAMPBELL AND KATE MOSS IN
THIS 1996 WHITE TRENCH.
ANNA WINTOUR SAID HIS CREATIVE
GENIUS WAS BREATH TAKING AND TO
BE HIS FRIEND WAS AN
EXCEPTIONAL GIFT.
HE WAS SO ECCENTRIC, TOO HE
DESIGNED COKE BOTTLES.
THEY NEVER HIT IT BUT HE SAID
I'M A PEPSI DRINKER EVEN THOUGH
I DESIGNED COKE BOTTLES.
>> I ALSO LOVED THAT HE BROUGHT
HIS FASHION TO THE PEOPLE.
THERE WAS A LINE AT MACY'S,
WHICH IS THE ONLY REASON WHY I
WORE A DRESS.
>> HE HAD A COLLECTION WITH
H&M, TOO.
>> HE SOMEHOW IS RELEVANT FOR
DECADES AND DECADES IN FASHION.
THAT'S HARD TO DO.
HE'S CLOSE TO  KENDALL JENNER
AND ALL THE WAY BACK.
>> YES, YES, YES.
>>> CHICAGO DETECTIVES ARE
STILL INVESTIGATING THE JUSSIE
SMOLLETT CASE.
>> Reporter: SAM, WE'RE GETTING
MORE CLUES IN THE JUSSIE
SMOLLETT CASE.
MULTIPLE PORESES TELL THEM THE
"EMPIRE QCT ACTOR SET IT UP
BECAUSE THIS RACIST LETTER
DIDN'T GET A BIGGER ROW ACTION.
HE SAID HIS SCENES ON EMPIRE
ARE BEING PULLED.
HE WAS SUPPOSED TO HAVE NINE
SCENES.
THE PRODUCTION SOURCES TELL TMZ
THEY HAVE NOW BEEN CUT.
CHICAGO POLICE ARE LOOKING TO
SIT DOWN WITH JUSSIE FOR MORE
QUESTIONING.
>> ERICA, I SAW YOUR BODY
LANGUAGE CHANGE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SEE.
YOU SEE HIS LIFE IMPLODING
BEFORE ALL OF OUR EYES AND THE
IDEA THAT THIS COULD BE A HOAX,
I HAVE NO WORDS.
>> IT'S JAW DROPPING.
>> I HAVE NO WORDS.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE HERE
BUT HERE WE ARE.
LIKE DR. DREW SAID LAST WEEK
WHEN HE WAS ON OUR PANEL IF
THIS TURNS OUT TO BE A HOAX,
LET'S HOPE HE GET THE HELP HE
NEEDS.
HE DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
>> HE'S ALIENATED THE BLACK
COMMUNITY, GAY COMMUNITY.
I WORRY ABOUT HIM BECAUSE HE
MUST HAVE SOME MENTAL PROBLEMS.
>> ARE YOU OKAY, ERICA?
AN EYELASH FELL.
IT SEEMED VERY EMOTIONAL.
>> I THINK IT'S AN EYELASH.
>> THAT'S NOT THE EXCUSE A GUY
GIVES.
>> "DBL" LIVE.
COMING UP OSCAR WINNER CHARLIZE
THERON IS THE NEW BEER FACE.
>> AND SOCIAL MEDIA SITES BE
RESPONSIBLE FOR IDENTIFYING
MISIDENTIFICATION.
YOUR COMMENTS COMING UP NEXT.
>> "DAILY BLAST LIVE" AND
SANDALS RESORTS WANT YOU TO
FALL IN LOVE ALL OVER AGAIN.
WE'RE GIVING AWAY A TRIP TO YOU
AND YOUR SPECIAL LOVED ONE TO
ONE OF THE SECLUDED HOT SPOTS.
JUST WATCH "DBL" FOR THE WORD
OF THE DAY AND GO TO "DAILY
BLAST LIVE"/SANDALS.
THE WINNER WILL BE ANNOUNCED
LIVE ON FEBRUARY 27th.
HOW COULD YOU NOT LOVE THAT.
Z35WHZ Z16FZ
Y35WHY Y16FY
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "DBL."
A NEW STUDY SUGGESTS YOUTUBE IS
PLAYING A SIGNIFICANT ROLE IN
CONVINCING PEOPLE THAT THE
EARTH IS FLA.
RESEARCHERS SAID IT'S EASY TO
GO DOWN A RABBIT HOLE OF
MISINFORMATION BECAUSE THE SITE
SUGGESTS A LOT OF INFORMATION.
SO IT'S TIME TO HEAR YOUR
COMMENTS IN FIFTH HOST.
>> HUGH SAID I BELIEVE IT
SHOULD BE THE RESPONSIBILITY OF
ALL OF US TO GET THE FALSE
INFORMATION OUT OF SOCIAL
MEDIA.
I AGREE.
YOU AND I BOTH HAVE THAT TIME.
I THINK FALSE INFORMATION IS
PART OF WHAT MAKES UP SOCIAL
MEDIA AND THE INTERNET ITSELF.
I THINK WE SHOULD START
TRUSTING SCIENTISTS, START
TROTTING EXPERTS IN THEIR
FIELD.
NO ONE HAS A THEORY WHEN IT
COMES TO FIXING YOUR
TRANSMISSION.
YOU GO TO A SPECIALIST.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
JOHN SAID IT'S UP TO YOU TO DO
YOUR RESEARCH AND NOT BE
GUMMABLE.
IT'S NOT YOUTUBE'S FAULT.
I COMPLETELY AFREE WITH JOHN.
YOU CAN GET UP AND WALK AWAY
FROM YOUTUBE.
YOU'RE NOT IN PRISON TO WATCH.
IT TWO, FREEDOM OF IMPRESSION,
FREEDOM OF SPEECH.
>> WHAT IF IT GETS DANGEROUS.
WHEN THIS COMES TO LIKE
ANTIVACCINE -- MY SISTER
BROUGHT THIS TO MY ATTENTION.
SHE'S A NURSE.
THERE'S BEEN A NUMBER OF YOUNG
KIDS IN REMISSION FROM CANCER
THAT HAVE DIED, FOUR THAT I
HAVE COUNT BECAUSE THEIR
COMPROMISED IMMUNE SYSTEMS,
THEY GOT THE  MEASLES.
>> THE TWO WORDS I WANT YOU TO
KNOW, ACTUAL MALICE.
I KNOW IT'S FALSE AND I
KNOWINGLY STILL PRODUCE IT.
THAT'S HARD TO PROVE.
YOU CAN SAY  ANTIVAXERS ARE
TRYING TO PROVE IT.
>> ASHLEY ON TWITTER SAID, YES.
FALSE NEWS SHOULD NEVER BE
SPREAD.
GARBAGE IN, GARBAGE OUT.
THAT'SY CHOOSE TO PUT MORE
POSITIVE THINGS IN.
>> YOU HAVE YOUR OWN ALGORITHM.
YOU DO IT ON YOUR INSTAGRAM.
>> IF YOU'RE FOLLOWING THE SAME
KIND OF PEOPLE AND THEY AREN'T
PROJECTING POSITIVE THINGS,
THEN THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
GETTING.
GIGI, GARBAGE IN, GARBAGE OUT.
THAT'S BACK IN BETA.
>> AND WE HAVE NEWS.
>> ARIANA GRANDE IS THE FIRST
SINCE THE BEATLES TO HAVE THE
ONE AND TWO SONG ON BILLBOARD
CHARTS, BREAK UP NUMBER TWO AND
THANK U NEXT AT NUMBER THREE.
SO I HAVE A LITTLE QUIZ FOR
YOU.
CAN YOU NAME THOSE THREE
BEATLES HITS?
>> TORY?
>> COME TOGETHER.
I'M GOING TO SAY I WANT TO HOLD
YOUR HAND AND I LOVE YOU YEAH,
YEAH, YEAH.
>> THOSE ARE ALL GREAT SONGS,
TORY BUT THEY'RE ALL WRONG.
>> IT WAS CAN'T BUY ME LOVE.
TWIST AND SHOUT AND DO YOU WANT
TO KNOW A SECRET.
>> I DON'T KNOW DO YOU WANT TO
NOLA SECRET INTO DO YOU KNOW A
SECRET.
>> THAT'S HOW TO GOES?
WEIRD.
COMING UP, A STICKY SITUATION
THAT WAS A MATTER OF LIFE AND
DEATH.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHAT HAPPENED TO
A GUY WHO WAS CAUGHT IN
QUICKSAND AND TORY GOES ONE ON
ONE WITH ALICE FROM "LITTLE
HOUSE ON THE PRAIRIE."
SHE CONFESSES WHAT IT WAS LIKE
TO PLAY TELEVISION'S ORIGINAL
BAD GIRL.
>>> TODAY'S WATCH AND WIN WORD
IS ROMANCE.
>> "LITTLE HOUSE ON THE
PRAIRIE" SPARKS NOSTALGIA.
ONE OF THE CHARACTERS WAS THE
BITTER BULLY IN A BONNET, NASTY
NELLIE OLSON.
IN TODAY'S CHATTING UP WITH THE
STARS, TV LEGENDS.
WELL, MY NIGHTMARES HAVE COME
THROUGH AND I'M HERE WITH
NELLIE.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
I WANTED TO ASK YOU ABOUT
"LITTLE HOUSE ON THE PRAIRIE,"
WHOLESOME SHOW BUT YOU WERE THE
ORIGINAL MEAN GIRL.
>> FROM THE ORIGINAL 1800'S.
>> WHAT WAS IT LIKE PLAYING
THAT.
>> I HADN'T READ THE BOOKS.
I WAS CLUELESS.
I TURNED TO MY FATHER AND SAID
THIS IS NOT A NORMAL PART.
SO I GO IN.
IT'S MICHAEL ANTHONY.
I READ THE THING AND THEY'RE
LAUGHING HISTORICALLY.
LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY.
THEY ASKED ME TO READ IT AGAIN
AND I ASKED WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO CHANGE.
>> WHO'S YOUR FAVORITE TV
VILLAIN NOW.
>> THERE ARE SOME GOOD ONES.
IT'S SHAD THAT KING GEOFFREY
HAD TO DIE AT THE WEDDING.
PEOPLE WERE WRITING TO ME.
ARE YOU GUYS RELATED BECAUSE HE
LOOKS LIKE HE COULD BE MY
FREAKING KID AND EVERYONE WAS
DOING EVIL HAS A FACE, MY
PICTURE AND GEOFFREY.
OKAY.
I THOUGHT HE WAS BRILLIANT.
>> YOU HAVE A ONE WOMAN SHOW.
>> I DO, CONFESSIONS OF A
PRAIRIE B. IT'S BASED AND NEW
YORK TIME'S BEST SELLER.
>> WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE.
>> YOU'RE THAT SUCH GOOD OF AN
ACTRESS.
>> THANK YOU.
THIS IS THE BIG THING, LOVING
TO HATE YOU.
LOVING TO LOVE AND HATE IT.
>> YOU GUYS SPENT SO MUCH TIME
TOGETHER S THERE ANYTHING FUNNY
BEHIND THE SCENES?
>> CONSTANTLY.
WE HAD MICHAEL LANDON WHO WAS
THE BIGGEST PRACTICAL JOKER IN
THE WORLD.
I THINK HE LIKED WORKING WITH
THE KIDS BEST, BECAUSE HE WAS
LIKE A 12-YEAR-OLD AT HEART.
HE WAS OBSESSIVE AND BANANAS.
>> IT WORKED.
>> THIS WORKED.
THAT'S WHY THE SHOW WAS SO
GOOD.
SOMEONE HAD TO BE THAT DRIVEN
AND ON IT TO MAKE THIS WORK.
THE LITTLE HOUSE BOOKS, THEY'RE
GREAT BUT THE TV SHOW, HOW
BORING COULD THAT HAVE BEEN.
>> THE PACING.
>> THAT COULD HAVE BEEN MIGHTY
SLOW.
>> THAT'S A FAIR POINT.
>> IF YOU LIKED ANYBODY AT
LITTLE HOUSE, HE PICKED HIM.
>> NO SCANDAL.
>> NO.
>> THANK YOU.
I'VE NEVER ENJOYED AN INTERVIEW
MORE.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> COMING UP ON "DBL," DITCH
THE POTS FULL OF GREASE.
WE'LL SHOW YOU THE HEALTHIER
WAY TO FRY WITH AIR TECHNOLOGY.
>> MEET A BOY WHO'S FULFILLING
HIS DREAM DESPITE HIS MEDICAL
CONDITION.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "DBL."
TODAY'S HEART THREADS ARE ALL
ABOUT PASSION.
WATCH HOW A YOUNG BOY IS
CONTINUING TO PLATE SPORT HE
LOVES.
A 10-YEAR-OLD HEART PATIENT HAD
HIS WISH COME TRUE.
ANDREW McDUFFY WAS BORN WITH
SERIOUS HEALTH PROBLEMS, HAVING
HIS FIRST SURGERY AT FOUR
MONTHS OLD.
JUST BEFORE HIS 10th BIRTHDAY
HE NEEDED ANOTHER SURGERY.
DOCTORS TOLD ANDERSON HE WAS
TOO FRAGILE FOR CONTACT SPORTS
BUT THAT DIDN'T END HIS DREAM
OF BECOMING A HOCKEY PLAYER.
>> THEY THINK I'M FRAGILE.
I TELL THEM I'M PERFECT.
I'M JUST AS FINALS THEM.
>> Reporter: THANKS TO MAKE-A-
WISH ANDERSON AND HIS TEAM, THE
EKG'S TOOK TO THE ICE.
THEY WON 6-5 AND ANDERSON EVEN
GOT TO FIGHT.
>> YOU WANT TO LIVE EVERY DAY
WITH FULL PASSION.
SO IF WE TELL HIM HE CAN'T PLAY
HOCKEY, THERE IS NO POINT IN
FIXING HIS HEART.
HE DOESN'T WANT TO LIVE
PROTECTED IN A BUBBLE.
>> HOW LONG ARE YOU GOING TO
REMEMBER THIS?
>> FOREVER.
>> HOW TRIUMPHANT.
>> I KNOW, BEING CARRIED OFF
LIKE.
THAT IT'S SOMETHING ABOUT
ATHLETES.
THEY HAVE A SENSE THEY ACCEPT
YOU.
HE'S DONE SUCH A GREAT JOB.
>> AND FOR HIM TO SAY THAT
MOMENT IS GOING TO CHANGE HIS
LIFE AND HE WILL REMEMBER IT
FOREVER.
>> YOU THINK ABOUT ATHLETES,
THEY'RE REAL LIFE SUPER HEROES.
THEY DO THINGS MOST OTHER
PEOPLE CAN'T DO ESPECIALLY
PEOPLE WHO ARE SICK.
IF HE CAN DO THAT, I CAN GET
OUT OF THIS HOSPITAL BED.
>> YOU CAN WATCH US LIVE ON
FACEBOOK AND YOUTUBE.
HERE'S WHAT'S COMING UP NEXT ON
"DBL."
>> MOVE OVER, SUPER BOWL.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHY THE HOTTEST
NEW COMMERCIALS INCLUDING ONE
WITH CHARLIZE THERON WILL BE
AIRED DURING THE OSCARS.
THEN A REAL LIFE STICKY
SITUATION.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN A MAN GOT STUCK IN
QUICKSAND AND CURLY HAIR.
MEET A TRAILBLAZER WHO'S MAKING
NATURAL HAIR THE NORM
Z35K8Z Z16FZ
Y35K8Y Y16FY