>>> THIS IS "DAILY BLAST LIVE."
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
ALWAYS LIVE, ALWAYS REAL,
ALWAYS UNPREDICTABLE.
>> YOU'RE TOTALLY OFF BASE
HERE.
>> LOG ON AND JOIN OURS
CONVERSATION.
>> I DO AGREE WITH YOU.
>> "DBL" STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> THREE, TWO --
>> WELCOME TO "DBL."
IT'S WEDNESDAY, FEBRUARY 6th.
LET'S GET STARTED.
ALL MONTH WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
YOUR FAVORITE TV LEGENDS FROM
THE PAST.
TODAY WE'RE KICKING IT OFF WITH
MARIANNE.
SHE DISHES ABOUT HER FORT HOOD
WITH GINGER AND WE'RE TALKING
TO RANDY FROM SAY YES TO THE
DRESS.
FIRST.
ALL EYES WERE ON THE PRESIDENT
AS HE DELIVERED HIS SECOND
STATE OF THE UNION ADDRESS.
HE STRUCK A WIDELY BIPARTISAN
STONE.
HOWEVER, THE PRESIDENT DID NOT
BUDGE ON HIS KEY PROMISE FOR A
WALL AND TOOK AIM AT THE
GROWING INVESTIGATIONS AROUND
HIM CALLING THEM RIDICULOUS AND
PARTISAN.
THERE WAS PAP MOMENT WHEN
DEMOCRATIC WOMEN CLAD IN WHITE
GOT TO THEIR FEET AND CHEERED.
>> WE HAVE MORE WOMEN IN THE
WORKFORCE THAN EVER BEFORE.
DON'T SIT YET.
YOU'RE GOING TO LIKE THIS.
WE ALSO HAVE MORE WOMEN SERVING
IN CONGRESS THAN AT ANYTIME
BEFORE.
>>> HOUSE SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI
CLAPPED BACK AT THE PRESIDENT
IN HER SIGNATURE MOVE THAT SET
THE INTERNET ON FIRE AT THE
MEMES HAVE BEEN COMING IN.
FINALLY WHEN I TELL MY WIFE I
CLEANED THE BATHROOM.
ONE OF THE PRESIDENT'S GUESTS,
AN 11-YEAR-OLD WHO WAS BULLIED
BECAUSE HIS LAST NAME IS
TRUMPED.
HE'S GOING VIRAL, TOO, BECAUSE
HE APPEARED TO FALL  LAY
ASLEEP.
HE'S A KID.
>> I THOUGHT HE WAS PREPARED.
HE HAD THE NAMES RIGHT.
I THOUGHT -- THAT'S A BIG
MESSUP WHEN THAT HAPPENS.
HE HAD PREPARED OBVIOUSLY FOR
THAT.
I LOVED IT WHEN THE WOMEN STOOD
UP BUT EVERYBODY ON BOTH SIDES
STARTED SCREAMING USA, USA.
IT WAS A GREAT MOMENT.
>> AND TO SEE THE WOMEN
REPRESENT, THANK GOD WE ARE
WHERE WE ARE TODAY.
WE HAVE MORE PROGRESS TO GO BUT
AN ODE TO THE SUFFRAGE
MOVEMENT.
>> THEY HIGHLIGHTEDDAL LIST
JOHNSON, THE BLACK WOMAN WHO
WAS EXONERATED FROM PRISON.
I HOPE SHE BECOMES THE FACE OF
A LOT OF PEOPLE BEHIND BARS.
THE NUMBER OF PEOPLE BEHIND
BARS IS STAGGERING.
WE HAVE A FOURTH OF THE PEOPLE
BEHIND BARS.
THIS COUNTRY IS BUILT ON
STOCKPILING HUMAN BEINGS AND
PUTTING THEM IN CAGES.
DON'T FORGET WHERE WE LIVE AND
THIS CAN BE FIXED.
>> PRISON REFORM.
WHAT DID YOU THINK?
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS GREAT.
I THOUGHT IT WAS POSITIVE FOR
THE MOST PART.
I'M RIGHT DOWN THE AISLE ON
THIS ONE.
I WISH THEY WOULD FOCUS MORE ON
THE PRESIDENT, NOT SO MUCH
NANCY PELOSI AND THE PEOPLE
CLAPPING.
I DIDN'T LIKE HOW A LOT OF
TIMES ONE SIDE WOULD STAND UP
AND THE OTHER WOULD SIT DOWN.
IF YOU'RE WATCHING AT HOME
YOU'RE NOT FORMULATING YOUR OWN
OPINION.
YOU DISMISS WHAT HE SAID.
I THINK A LOT OF WHAT HE SAID
WAS POSITIVE.
>> WHAT A GREAT POINT.
IT'S HARD TO BE AN INDEPENDENT
THINK ARE WHEN YOU'RE ALIGNED
WITH YOUR PARTY AND YOU SEE
YOUR PARTY STANDING.
HOW ARE YOU ABLE TO FORM AN
INDEPENDENT THOUGHT.
>> SO WHEN THEY STAND AND SIT,
IT'S TO SHOW RESPONSE.
I WILL SUPPORT THIS
LEGISLATION.
I WON'T.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
>> BUT IT'S BECOME MORE OF A
DRINKING GAME.
IT'S ALL ABOUT WHO STANDS AND
WHO DOESN'T.
>> WE WANT TO HEAR FROM YOU,
TOO, "DBL" NATION.
>> SEVERAL OF THE PRESIDENT'S
RIVALS ARE IN THE NEWS, CORY
BOOKER FINALLY ADMITTED HE'S
GOT A SPECIAL SOMEONE.
>> BEFORE I DECLARE SOMEONE,
I'M DATING SOMEONE VERY
SPECIAL.
>> CORY BOOKER'S GOT A BOO.
>> I LOVE IT.
CORY BOOKER'S GOT A BOO.
THERE'S A LOT OF SPECULATION
HIS BOO IS ROSARIO DAWSON.
THE TWO HAVE BEEN SEEN OUT
TOGETHER AT A BROADWAY SHOW.
>> OPRAH SAT DOWN WITH BETO
O'ROURKE.
SHE ENCOURAGED HIM TO RUN FOR
PRESIDENT AND GOT HIM TO AGREE
BEFORE THE END OF THE MONTH.
DOES IT STRIKE YOU THAT PEOPLE
DO CONSIDER WHICH CELEBRITY'S
ENDORSING A CANDIDATE?
FOR INSTANCE, IF OPRAH IS GOING
TO ENDORSE BETO O'ROURKE, WILL
THAT INCREASE HIS CHANCES OF
WINNING.
SAME, DOES IT HELP OR HURT TO
HAVE ROSARIO DAWSON, AN
ACTIVIST AND ACTRESS BY HIS
SIDE.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO SAY I'M A
FAN OF HIM OR NOT BUT I THINK
HAVING A CELEBRITY ON YOUR SIDE
HELPS.
IF YOU'RE ENDORSED BY OPRAH.
>> IS THAT THE BIGGEST
ENDORSEMENT YOU CAN GET?
>> OF COURSE.
I DON'T THINK THE TIMING IS A
COINCIDENCE WITHROSEROSARIO
DAWSON.
>> LET'S SAY SHE WENT TO THE
WHITE HOUSE WITH HIM, WHETHER
THEY'RE MARRIED OR JUST A
COUPLE.
SHE WOULD MAKE A GREAT, SO TO
SPEAK, FIRST LADY.
>> SHE ALREADY IS A MODERN
FIRST LADY.
SHE'S TECH LOGICALLY ADVANCED.
SHE WOULD BE A HUGE BOOST AND
IN TODAY'S CELEBRITY CULTURE.
>> SEE, AL THINKS DIFFERENT.
YOU THINK CELEBRITIES CAN HURT.
THEY ALMOST THINK CELEBRITIES
ALIGN WITH AN ELITIST MENTALITY
THAT'S UNRELATABLE.
DEPENDS ON THE CELEBRITY.
IS IT ROSARIO DAWSON OR TED
NUGENT.
NOT ONLY DO YOU WANT TO HAVE A
MAJOR CELEBRITY BUT THEN HAVING
SOME OF THESE SMALLER
INFLUENCERS.
WE SAW IT WORKED AT FIRE FEST.
IF YOU TELL PEOPLE TO DO IT,
THEY WILL DO IT.
>> MAKE SURE YOU'RE ALIGNED
WITH THEIR POLICIES.
SUSAN LUCCI IS OPENING UP ABOUT
A HEART SCARE.
SHE SAID SHE FELT LIKE AN
ELEPHANT STOMPING ON HER CHEST.
TESTS SHOWED A 90% BLOCK IN ONE
ARTERY AND 80% ON THE OTHER.
>> I ASKED THE DOCTOR HOW IS MY
HEART, MY ACTUAL HEART?
>> HE SAID YOUR HEART IS THAT
OF A 20-YEAR-OLD.
HE SAID IT THREE TIMES, SO I
BELIEVED HIM.
I'M GLAD I WANT HOME.
IF I WAS HOME I WOULD HAVE SAID
OH, I JUST NEED TO LAY DOWN.
>> FEBRUARY IS HEART MONTH.
PART OF THE REASON LUCCI IS
SPEAKING OUT, SHE HOPES OTHERS
WILL LEARN MORE ABOUT HEART
DISEASE.
IN ADDITION TO CHEST PAIN
THERE'S NAUSEA, VOLUME MITTING,
SWEATING, FATIGUE, SHORTNESS OF
BREATH.
KEYS TO REDUCE IT WEIGHT
MANAGEMENT, BEING ACTIVE,
REDUCING STRESS AND MORE.
>> THOSE ALL COMBINED WITH EACH
OTHER.
EXERCISING REDUCING STRESS.
IF YOU KEEP THE EXERCISE, I
THINK EVERYTHING ELSE WILL FALL
INTO PLACE.
>> AWARE NEXT TOO.
WHEN YOU THINK OF HEART ATTACK
YOU THINK ARM HURTING, RIGHT
ARM.
JAW PAIN.
A DENTIST WILL TELL SOMEONE YOU
NEED TO GO STRAIGHT TO THE
HOSPITAL.
MY GRANDFATHER HAD A QUADRUPLE
BYPASS.
IT SAVED HIS LIVE.
>> "DBL" IS LIVE.
COMING UP, MEGHAN MARKLE'S
FRIENDS ARE OPENING UP ABOUT
THE DUCHESS.
>> PLUS, DESIGNER RANDY TELLS
US HIS LEAST PART OF MEGHAN'S
WEDDING GOWN.
YOUR COMMENTS COMING UP NEXT.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "DBL."
BRIDES TAKING ON THEIR LAST
NAME OF THEIR PARTNERS IS AN
AGE-OLD TRADITION.
NOWADAYS NEWLY WEDS HAVE
OPTIONS.
DO YOU ADD A HYPHEN OR STICK TO
YOUR ROOTS.
SHE CHOSE WHY SHE CHOSE TO TAKE
ON HER HUSBAND'S NICK'S NAME.
SHE SAID IT FELT LIKE THE
BLENDING OF THE FAMILIES AND
DIDN'T WANT TO LOSE HER.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT DITCHING
THE LAST NAME FOR THE PARTNER.
>> ONE SAYS IF THE WOMAN IS
CONCERNED ABOUT THE POSSIBILITY
OF DIVORCE AND COMPLICATIONS
AFTERWARDS, THE SIMPLE SOLUTION
DON'T GET MARRIED.
THAT IS TAKING A HAMMER TO AN
ANT.
HE  REALLY WENT AFTER IT.
I GUESS THAT IS ONE WAY TO
AVOID THE ISSUE, BUT I DON'T
KNOW IF WE NEED TO ABOLISH
MARRIAGE.
>> JOHN FROM YOUTUBE SAID NO
WOMAN SHOULD BE OBLIGATED TO
DITCH THEIR LAST NAME.
I PLAN ON TAKING MY GIRL'S LAST
NAME.
THAT WILL MAKE ME JOHNNY RUSH.
HOW COOL DOES THAT SOUND.
MY GOD BROTHER TOOK HIS LAST
NAME JAGGER.
I KEPT MINE BECAUSE I'M A
COMEDIAN AND I THOUGHT PEOPLE
KNEW ME AS TORY SHULMAN.
WHY ARE YOU GUYS LAUGHING?
>> SHE SAID I WAS 42 WHEN I GOT
MARRIED.
I NEVER TOOK MY HUSBAND'S NAME.
HE NEVER GOT OVER IT.
>> MY WIFE, I THINK IS TOO LAZE
DI TO CHANGE HER LAST NAME.
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO GO TO THE
DMV OR CHANGE HER CREDIT CARDS.
I HAVE MY TWO SONS.
THEY HAVE MY LAST NAME.
I'M HAPPY.
>> THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IS
COMMUNICATION.
A LOT OF THE PROBLEMS ARISE
WHEN CHILDREN COME INTO PLAY.
I'M SCHACHER.
SOPHIE'S SCHACHER.
>> I HAVE A QUESTION TO ASK
DURING THE BREAK.
>> PERFECT.
ARIANA GRANDE IS CAUGHT UP WITH
SOME DPRA A.
>> ARIANA DRAMA.
>> VARIETY REPORTS SHE WAS
SUPPOSED TO PERFORM AT THE SHOW
BUT CLASHED WITH THE PRODUCERS
AFTER THEY REFUSED TO LET HER
SING HER LATEST SINGLE "SEVEN
RINGS."
SHE PULLED OUT WHEN THEY SAID
THEY WOULD BE CHOOSING SOME OF
THE SONGS.
SHE'S UP FOR TWO GRAMMYS ON
SUNDAY.
HER LATEST ALBUM IS OUT ON
FRIDAY.
>> THAT'S SOME PRETTY BIG
PLANS.
COMING UP, ONE ON ONE WITH TV
ROYALTY.
DAWN WELLS FROM GILLIGAN'S
ISLAND WEIGHS IN ON THAT FEUD
WITH GINGER.
>> AND THEN RANDY FENOLI FROM
"SAY YES TO THE DRESS."
WHAT TREND MAKES HIS SKIN CRAWL
AFTER THE BREAK.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
I NEED ALL BRIDES TO BE TO
LISTEN.
HOW DOES A FREE WEDDING AND A
TRIP TO THE ICONIC BRIDAL STORE
SOUND?
YOU CAN FIND OUT HOW AS I CATCH
UP WITH DESIGNER RANDY FENOLI
ABOUT HIS NEW TV SHOW.
RANDY FENOLI, WELCOME TO "DBL."
WHEN IT COMES TO WEDDING
DRESSES, YOU ARE THE END ALL,
BE ALL.
OF COURSE, FANS KNOW YOU
THROUGH "SAY YES TO THE DRESS"
BUT YOU'VE ALSO LAUNCHED BRIDAL
COLLECTIONS AND RECEIVED AWARDS
FOR YOUR DESIGNS.
I NEED TO KNOW YOUR THOUGHTS.
THE MOST FAMOUS WEDDING DRESS
OF 2019, MISS MEGHAN MARKLE.
IS THERE ANYTHING YOU WOULD
HAVE CHANGED?
>> FOR ME I THINKED VEIL WAS A
LITTLE TOO LONG BUT I THINK THE
DRESS FIT BEAUTIFULLY.
I WOULDN'T HAVE CHANGED
ANYTHING.
>> IT'S MORE ABOUT HELPING
BRIDES FIND A DRESS.
CAN YOU TELL US MORE.
WHAT MAKES IT DIFFERENT FROM
THE ORIGINAL "SAY YES TO THE
DRESS."
>> WE'RE ASKING FOR BRIDES ALL
ACROSS AMERICA TO SUBMIT A
VIDEO TO TLC.COM AND THEY WILL
HAVE AN ALL EXPENSE PAID TRIP
TO KLEINFELD AND A RECEPTION
FOR THE COUPLES AND THE
BIGGEST, GRANDEST, MOST
INCREDIBLE WEDDING CEREMONY IN
AMERICAN HISTORY, I BELIEVE.
>> TELL US IS UNFAIR.
I'M ALREADY MARRIED.
I WANT TO GET DIVORCED AND
REMARRIED JUST SO I CAN BE ON
THIS SHOW.
>> DON'T GET DIVORCED.
IF YOU HAVE AN INTERESTING
ENOUGH VIDEO, I MEAN, WE MIGHT
EVEN DO VOW RENEWALS.
SEND US A VIDEO.
>> I'M HAVING BUTTERFLIES.
SO YOU'LL BE HELPING 50 BRIDES
BE ON THE SHOW.
WHILE THAT MAY SOUND LIKE A
LOT, YOU'VE HELPED THOUSANDS
AND THOUSANDS OF WOMEN.
IF THERE'S ONE TREND YOU WISH
WOULD DIE, WHICH TREND WOULD IT
BE?
>> I THINK BASICALLY THE ENTIRE
1980s, THE SLEEVES, HIGH WASTE,
FULL GATHERED SKIRT WITH LACE
APPLIQUES ALL OVER.
I'M GLAD WE CAN FORGET THE
1980s IN FASHION.
>> I AGREE.
RANDY, THANK YOU FOR CATTING
WITH US.
CHATTING WITH US.
YOU CAN HAVE RANDY, A DREAM
COME TRUE.
SEND IT TO TLC.COM/CASTING.
>> COMING UP, TYRA BANKS IS
TAKING A PAGE OUT OF THE WALT
DISNEY PLAYBOOK AND "DBL" DRIVE
COMING UP NEXT.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "DBL."
WELL, PHIL THE GROUNDHOG HAS
SPOKEN AND WE HAVE TALKED ABOUT
HOW WINTER WILL BE SHORTER THIS
YEAR.
THIS IS PRESENTED BY CAR
SHIELD.
OUR BROTHER FROM ANOTHER
MOTHER, PUNXSUTAWNEY PHIL DID
NOT SEE HIS SHADOW.
>> NO SHADOW.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK THAT MEANS
IN.
>> I THINK WE'RE TRUSTING A
RODENT MORE THAN SCIENTISTS.
>> THESE SCIENTISTS HAVE BEEN
HERE LONGER THAN SHINE TISES
AND THEY HAVE SOMETHING CALLED
NATURE INSTINCTS.
>> HOW DID THAT WORK OUT FOR
THE DINOSAURS.
>> THEY SAID WE'RE DONE.
>> SPRING IS IN THE AIR.
WE HAVE TIPS TO ENJOY THE
WARMER WEATHER.
GET THE INDOOR CHORES DONE SO
WHEN THE GOOD WEATHER ROLLS IN
YOU'RE READY TO EXPLORE.
GET OUTSIDE AND ENJOY THE EARLY
SUNSHINE.
NO MATTER WHAT THE SEASON,
DRIVE WITH PEACE OF MIND AND
GET A PLAN WITH CARSHIELD.
CALL 1-800-505-9619 FOR A FREE
QUOTE.
>> I LOVE WATCHING THE TWO OF
YOU IN A CAR.
>> WE LOVE IT.
PUNXSUTAWNEY PHIL DID NOT SEE
HIS SHADOW WHICH SCIENTIFICALLY
MEANS MORE SPRING.
SPRING WILL BE SOONER.
AL GOES WHERE IN PENNSYLVANIA
DO YOU THINK HE'S FROM?
PUNXSUTAWNEY PHIL.
>> THIS IS COMING UP NEXT.
>> WOULD YOU GO TO A SUPER
MODEL THEME PARK?
TYRA BANKS IS HOPING YOU WILL.
THEN WE'RE CATCHING UP WITH TV
LEGEND DAWN WELLS, AKA FROM
GILLIGAN'S ISLAND, WHAT SHE
REALLY THOUGHT ABOUT GINGER AND
HER MONEY TROUBLES AFTER THE
SHOW ENDED AND "DBL" IS KEEPING
YOU YOUNG.
WE'RE