THIS  IS DAILY BLAST LIVE.
>> WE ARE TALKING ABOUT WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
>>  ALWAYS LIVE, ALWAYS REAL,
ALWAYS UNPREDICTABLE.
>> LOG ON AND JOIN OUR LIVE
CONVERSATION.
>> DBL STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>>  WELCOME TO DBL MONDAY,
FEBRUARY 4 AND WE ARE LIVE AND
TALKING ABOUT WHAT YOU ARE
TALKING ABOUT, I'M HERE WITH
TORY, JEFF, AL AND I'M SAM .
EVERYONE IS TALKING ABOUT THE
SUPER BOWL AND IF YOU'RE JUST
JOINING US BECAUSE YOU ARE ONE
OF THE 17 MILLION WHO CALLED IN
SICK TODAY, WE ARE BREAKING ON
THE BIG GAME FOR YOU.
HEADLINES AROUND THE COUNTRY
ARE SAYING NOT AGAIN REFERRING
TO THE PATRIOTS LATEST SUPER
BOWL WIN, THE NEW YORK POST RAN
SUPER BOARD AND A DULL HALFTIME
CHEST, WHAT WE DIDN'T NEED IS A
SNOOZER BOWL, THE LOS ANGELES
TIMES CALLED IT'S HOMETOWN TEAM
LAMBS, NOT RAMS AFTER THEY LOST
13-3.  PATRIOTS QUARTERBACK TOM
BRADY PROVED HE'S A CHAMPION
CELEBRATE AS HIS 6th WIN WITH
THE KISS FROM HIS WIFE GISELE
AND TOOK HIS DAUGHTER WITH HIM
TO THE STAGE WHEN THE TEAM WAS
PRESENTED WITH THE VINCENT
PARTY TROPHY.
ONE THING EVERYONE AGREED ON WAS
THE RENDITION OF THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM WAS WIDELY APPLAUDED,
TAKE A LISTEN.
♪ ♪ ♪ ONE THING THAT WAS
ALMOST UNIVERSALLY CRITICIZED
AND BECAME THE BUTT OF MANY
SOCIAL MEDIA JOKES WAS MAROON
5'S HALFTIME SHOW WHICH WAS
CALLED CONVENTIONAL, TEPID IN
THE MUSICAL EQUIVALENT OF A JAR
OF MAYONNAISE.
YOU BE THE JUDGE, CHECK OUT THE
CLIP.
>> ♪ ♪ ♪ AND TRAVIS SCOTT
ALSO MADE A BRIEF APPEARANCE
SINGING HIS HIT SONG SICKLE
MODE, A LOT OF IT WAS BLEEPED
OUT FOR CONTENT.
BIG BOI MADE A GRAND ENTRANCE
OUTKASTBUT IN REAL DIDN'T
HAPPEN LIKE MAMA MUCH OF US
HOPED AND SPONGEBOB FANS WERE
HAPPY WHEN A CLIP OF SWEET
VICTORY PLAYED BRIEFLY, FOR THE
BIGGEST HALFTIME SHOW
CONTROVERSY, THIS MOMENT WHEN
ADAM LEVINE STRIPPED OF HIS TOP
WITH MANY SAYING IT'S A DOUBLE
STANDARD FOLLOWING THE BACKLASH
JANET JACKSON RECEIVED AFTER
ACCIDENTALLY EXPOSING ONE FOR
BREASTS AND SPEAKING OF THE
TANK TOP, TWITTER WAS QUICK TO
POINT OUT OVER AND OVER THAT IT
VERY CLEARLY RESEMBLES PEOPLE'S
HOME DECOR LIKE THIS PILLOW,
AND OTHERS WERE QUICK TO SHOW
THAT ADAMS TATTOOS LOOK A LOT
LIKE TRIPLE PLAY BAGS.
ADAM IS RESPONDING TO ALL THE
HATERS A POSTING INSTAGRAM
SAYING WE THINK THE UNIVERSE
FOR THIS HISTORIC OPPORTUNITY
TO PLAY ON THE WORLD'S BIGGEST
STAGE AND WE THINK OUR FANS FOR
MAKING OUR DREAMS POSSIBLE AND
WE THINK CRITICS FOR ALWAYS
PUSHING US TO DO BETTER.
>>> HE'S A LOT CLASSIER THAN I
AM.
>> I WOULD JUST TWEET BACK HEY
I WAS DOING THE SUPER BOWL AND
I MISS THESE TWEETS, WHAT WERE
YOU DOING?
HONESTLY, HE JUST OF THE SUPER
BOWL AND THAT'S A BIG DEAL.
AS AN ARTIST THAT'S THE
PINNACLE.
HE DID IT.
>> OUT YOU ARE VERY HARD ON HIM
AND MAROON 5 AND LAST NIGHT I
WAS HONORED TO BE AT A SUPER
BOWL PARTY WITH YOU.
>> AS YOU SHOULD BE.
>>> WHILE I DID THINK THE SHOW
WAS ENJOYABLE I FELT I WAS A
LITTLE BIASED BECAUSE I SAW MY
DAUGHTER DANCING AND THAT'S ALL
I CARED ABOUT.
I WAS SURPRISED TO SEE NO JOE,
ELBOWS OUT COMING THROUGH THE
CROWD, FRONT ROW, YOU ARE LIKE
THAT WAS AWESOME.
YOU THOUGHT IT WAS THE MOST
AWESOME EXPERIENCE YOU'VE EVER
SEEN BASED ON YOUR REACTION.
>> DADDY WAS FEELING NO PAIN.
IT WAS SUCH A GOOD MOMENT, I
LOOKED AROUND, I SAW LAWSON AND
SOPHIE DANCING, YOUR 2 CHILDREN
AND YOU ARE FEELING IT.
WE HAVE THE VIDEO?  THERE IS
SAM RIGHT THERE.
SAME AS DANCING, YOU ARE
FEELING IT.
>> I HAVE TO BE HONEST.
>> THERE IS LAWSON GETTING ON
THE FLOOR.
>> THAT'S WHAT'S UP.
AND A SCENE.
>>> I HAVE TO ADMIT, I CAN ADMIT
THERE WAS A BIT OF A BIAS LAST
NIGHT, I THOUGHT IT WAS THE
MOST INCREDIBLE PERFORMANCE
BECAUSE OF SOPHIE AND LAWSON
BUT I WATCH THE BACK THIS
MORNING AND IT WAS A LITTLE
LACKLUSTER, JUST BEING HONEST.
>>> I KNOW YOU'RE WAITING FOR
ME TO HATE ON IT BUT I LIKED
IT, I THOUGHT IT WAS TERRIFIC,
AND THE 5 MINUTE INTRO, WITH
ALL THE NEGATIVE COMMENTS, GOOD
FOR MAROON 5 FOR NOT FIRING
BACK AND BEING POSITIVE, I
THOUGHT IT WAS A GREAT SHOW,
EVERYONE WANTS EVERYONE TO PUSH
THE LINE AND THIS IS WHAT
AMERICA NEED IT, THERE WAS NO
POLITICS, I THOUGHT IT WAS A
GREAT SHOW.
HE IS 39, IF I LOOK LIKE THAT I
WOULD DO THE SHOW WITH NO SHIRT
ON RIGHT NOW.
I THOUGHT HE DID A GREAT JOB.
AND I REALLY ENJOYED IT, I
THOUGHT HE DID A GREAT JOB.
ALL THE HATERS GET REAL.
>> T-BONE.
>> 04.
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE HATER.
>> BE HONEST WHAT DID YOU
THINK?
>> I THINK I HALFTIME SHOW YOU
SHOULD BE AT THE BEST OF YOUR
VERY BEST I THINK HE WAS
LACKLUSTER AND NON-ENERGETIC
AND SEEMED PERFECTLY UNHAPPY TO
BE HONEST.
I WOULD'VE BEEN SO EXCITED TO
COME HERE AND BE LIKE MAROON 5.
THEY DID GREAT.
I WAS SUPER BORED AND
DISAPPOINTED.
>> THAT'S HOW I FELT.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> EVERYONE IS COMPLAINING SO
MUCH, GOOD LUCK NEXT YEAR WHEN
THERE'S NO SUPER BOWL HALFTIME
SHOW, LIKE THE OSCARS WITH NO
HOST THIS YEAR.
>> NO HOST FOR THE OSCARS.
>> WHY WOULD THERE NOT BE A
SUPER BOWL HALFTIME SHOW?
>> WHO WILL PERFORM.
NO MATTER WHAT THEY DO, YOU
WANT ELVIS TO COME UP FROM THE
GRAVE?
>> TO BE HONEST I WANTED LADY
GAGA WHO JUMPED OFF HER PRINCE
WHO SANG WITH AMAZING
PERFORMANCES, YOU HAVE TO OWN
IT.
>> HOW MANY PRINCES AND LADY
GAGA'S ARE THERE?
>> I THINK HE OWNED IT, IT
DOESN'T MEAN I'M A HORRIBLE
PERSON PER
>> YOU'RE KIND OF INSINUATING
THAT.
>> SHARE YOUR COMMENTS ON THE
BIG GAME LATER ON 5th HOST BUT
FOR NOW WE WILL SWITCH GEARS TO
HARDER NEWS, CALLS FROM BOTH
SIDES OF THE AISLE FOR
VIRGINIA'S DEMOCRATIC GOVERNOR
TO RESIGN, KELLY SCHUBERTH HAS
MOVED NEWS OF THE MOMENT.
>>> THE WALLS CLOSING IN ON THE
GOVERNOR VIRGINIA AFTER RECESS
PHOTO FROM HIS 1984 MEDICAL
SCHOOL YEARBOOK SURFACED.
HERE'S A LOOK SHOWING ONE
PERSON IN BLACK FACE AND
ANOTHER IN A WHITE HOOD,
SHORTLY AFTER IT WAS RELEASED
HE ADMITTED IT WAS HIM IN THE
PHOTO BUT THEN IN A PRESS
CONFERENCE OVER THE WEEKEND HE
CHANGED HIS STORY SAYING HE DID
NOT WEAR THE COSTUME AND IT'S
DEFINITELY NOT HIM IN THE PHOTO
, AND HE'S SORRY BECAUSE IT
SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN PUBLISHED
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I WILL KEEP YOU UPDATED ON THE
DEVELOPING STORY.
>>> WE WON'T GET INTO IT BUT WE
CAN AGREE THIS GUY HAS TO STEP
DOWN?
>> IT'S UNACCEPTABLE, STEP
DOWN.
>>> ELECTED OFFICIALS SHOULD BE
HELD TO A HIGHER STANDARD, GET
OUT OF THERE.
>>> THAT'S A LOW STANDARD,
DON'T WEAR BLACK FACE.
>>> YES.
>>> WE HAVE VERY SAD NEWS FOR
ALL OR SOAP OPERA FANS, YOUNG
AND THE RESTLESS STAR KRISTOFF
ST. JOHN FOUND DEAD YESTERDAY
IN HIS HOME IN LOS ANGELES, HE
WAS 52.
HE PLAYED THE CHARACTER NEIL
WINTERS ON THE SOAP SINCE 1991,
HE WAS NOMINATED FOR 9 DAYTIME
EMMYS AND 110 DOUBLE ACP AWARDS
FOR HIS PORTRAYAL, THERE IS NO
WORD ON THE CAUSE OF HIS DEATH,
HE LOST HIS SON JULIAN ST. JOHN
TO SUICIDE IN 2014, THIS ONE
HURTS BECAUSE I'M A HUGE YOUNG
AND THE RESTLESS FAN AND I FEEL
LIKE I GREW UP WITH NEIL, I
KNEW HIM AND I KNOW A LOT OF OUR
DBL NATION AND FANS PROBABLY
FEEL THE SAME.
>> SOAP OPERAS ARE SO WEIRD,
YOU SEE IT MINUTELY DAY BY DAY,
MY MOM'S BEST FRIEND SOUGHT
EVERY DAY IN HER SHOP, WHEN ONE
GOES IT'S PART OF YOUR FAMILY
HAS LEFT.
WE DON'T KNOW THE CIRCUMSTANCES
BUT WE HOPE IF YOU ARE FEELING
LOW AND SAD, SALMON I'VE BEEN
SO OPEN, WE BEEN THERE, DO NOT
BE ASHAMED, WE HAVE SOMETHING
TO SHOW YOU, MENTAL HEALTH LIST
IF YOU NEED IT.
EVEN TEXTING, SOMETIMES YOU
CAN'T TALK, TEXT HOME, 74741.
>>> VERY IMPORTANT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>>
When was the last time
you felt...
Free.
It's time to uncover
that feeling again.
With the compassion and
strength of a name...
Most accepted by top doctors
and specialists.
And the power of a card...
that opens doors in
all fifty states.
Giving you the freedom to love
to dream to dance
Like no one is watching.
CareFirst
Blue Cross Blue Shield.
Live fearless.
THIS FEBRUARY, DAILY BLAST LIVE
AND SANDALS RESORT WANTS YOU TO
FALL IN LOVE ALL OVER AGAIN.
GIVING AWAY A TRIP FOR YOU IN
YOUR SPECIAL SOMEONE TO ONE OF
SANDALS LUXURY INCLUDED
VACATION HOTSPOTS.
ALL YOU NEED TO DO IS WATCH DBL
FOR THE WORD OF THE DAY.
AND GO TO
DAILYBLASTLIVE.COM/SANDALS TO
ENTER.
THE MORE WORDS THE MORE CHANCES
TO WIN.
THE WINNER WILL BE ANNOUNCED
LIVE ON DBL FEBRUARY 27.
HOW COULD YOU NOT LOVE THAT?
>> WELCOME BACK TO DBL TIME FOR
TODAY'S 5th HOST, THE INTERNET
IS ON FIRE WITH COMMENTS ABOUT
THE SUPER BOWL HALFTIME SHOW.
EVEN WITH THE HELP OF TRAVIS
SCOTT, BIG BOI AND SPONGEBOB,
CRITIC'S BLASTING MAROON 5'S
PERFORMANCE IN ADAM LEVINE FOR
BEING SHORT LIST.
DESPITE HARSH CRITICS LIVING
RESPONDED BY THINKING THE
UNIVERSE ALONG WITH A LAUNDRY
LIST OF WORDS INCLUDING
FORGIVE, LAUGH, CRY, SMILE AND
INTO HER.
DBL NATION WE WANT TO KNOW YOUR
TAKE ON THE HALFTIME SHOW,
LET'S GET YOUR COMMENTS.
>>>  RENI SAYS THE MOST
ENTERTAINING PART OF THE SUPER
BOWL WERE IN THE LADIES.
GLADYS KNIGHT AND THE SISTERS
CHLOE AND HALEY.
THE NATIONAL ANTHEM WAS
BEAUTIFUL, RENI, YOU HIT IT OUT
OF THE PARK YOU ARE RIGHT.
I THOUGHT GLADYS KNIGHT STOLE
THE SHOW, HEARING HER VOICE,
THE NATIONAL TREASURE IS ALWAYS
BEEN HERE.
YOU KIND OF FORGET.
I WILL GO STREAM SOME GLADYS
KNIGHT TONIGHT.
>>> CARRY FROM FACEBOOK SAYS I
LOVED MAROON 5, YOU CAN'T
PLEASE ANYONE, ADAM LEVINE
ROCKED, MY SISTER SO MAD, SHE
LOVED IT.
IF YOU'RE STEPPING UP STEP IT
UP AND I DIDN'T THINK THEY DID.
>>> SELENA FROM FACEBOOK SAYS
IT WAS THE WORST HALFTIME SHOW
EVER.
ADAM LEVINE IS NOT CUTE OR SEXY.
WE COULD'VE DONE WITHOUT THE
RHYTHM WITH MOVES.
>> HE DIDN'T HAVE MOVE LIKE
JAGER?
>> APPARENTLY NOT.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I'M SHOCKED,
SOCIAL MEDIA IS A NASTY PLACE
BUT I'M SURPRISED BY HOW MUCH
PEOPLE HATED THIS PERFORMANCE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY WANTED,
WHAT DO YOU WANT AND WHO DO YOU
WANT?
THE MORE YOU CRITICIZE PEOPLE
LIKE THIS THE LESS PEOPLE WILL
BE INTERESTED IN DOING A
HALFTIME SHOW.
I KNOW SAM THINKS IT'S A MUTE
POINT BUT WE DON'T HAVE A HOST
FOR THE OFFICERS BECAUSE OF
THIS POINT.
GOOD LUCK BASHING EVERYONE WHO
DOES EVERYTHING EVER IN THEIR
LIFE.
>>> YOU HAVE A GREAT POINT OUT.
MAYBE IT'S REPETITION AND I'M
FINALLY LISTENING BUT I THINK
YOU A VALID POINT.
>> IT'S ONE SHOW.
>> YOU ARE WELCOME.
>> THANK YOU FOR LISTENING.
>>> IT WAS A GOOD POINT THE
FIRST TIME WE ALWAYS JUMP ON
TORY'S BANDWAGON AND I'M THE
BAD GUY.
>>>  YOU LOOK AT ME LIKE A DEER
IN HEADLIGHTS.
>>> WHEN I'M IN THE
CONVERSATION AND TORY DISAGREES
MAYBE ONE TIME SAY HEY TORY
JEFF IS LITTLE RIGHT.
>>> I AM SORRY I JUST HAVE TO
SAY, WHEN YOU ARE LIKE WHAT DID
YOU WANT, I WANTED TO BE WELL
AND I THINK IT'S OKAY TO WANT
THAT.
>>> IT'S OKAY TO WANT THAT.
>>> IS SOMEONE CAME TO YOU IN
THEIR LIKE WE WILL GIVE YOU A
FREE SHOW, ADAM LEVINE,
MULTIMILLION DOLLAR SET UP,
WE'LL BRING BIG BOI AND TRAVIS
SCOTT AND EVERYONE'S LIKE  I'M
OVER IT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
IT'S FREE ENTERTAINMENT.
>> HE LOOKED TERRIFIC, I DON'T
KNOW.
>> HE DOES LOOK GREAT.
>>> WAS THE WORD, NOT
SPORTSMANSHIP, STAGE PRESENCE.
>>> SHOWMANSHIP COST THANK YOU,
I DON'T THINK IT WAS THERE.
>>> BECAUSE HE'S ONLY BEEN
PERFORMING 25 YEARS.
>>> THAT'S MY OPINION AND I'M
STICKING TO IT.
>>> YOU CAN I'M JUST SAYING I'M
SURPRISED HOW MUCH PEOPLE WERE
OUTRAGED.
>>> ON THE GETS FINE.
>>> HOW MANY TIMES WILL PEOPLE
KEEP REPEATING THEMSELVES.
>> 35 COMMENTS IN THE FATTEST
FIRST 5 MINUTES OF THE SHOW,
WE'VE GOT IT.  IT LOOKS LIKE A
PILLOW.
>>> J LO CELEBRATING A SPECIAL
ANNIVERSARY WITH HER MAN.
RAQUEL VILLANUEVA HAS ALL THE
DETAILS.
>>> JENNIFER LOPEZ CELEBRATING
HER ANNIVERSARY WITH  ALEX
RODRIGUEZ, SHARING A SWEET NOTE
WITH FAMILY PHOTOS AND BEHIND
THE SCENES MOMENTS, IT'S BEEN 2
YEARS SINCE THEY STARTED
TEAMING UP TO BECOME THE POWER
COUPLE J ROD AND SHE SAID THE
FORMER BASEBALL PLAYER MAKES
HER FEEL LIKE A TEENAGER ALL
OVER AGAIN, THEY ARE ALWAYS
SEEN SUPPORTING EACH OTHER AT
EVENTS AND MOST RECENTLY THEY
PUT US ALL TO SHAME WHEN THEY
WENT ON A 10 DAY CHALLENGE TO
EAT NO SUGAR AND CARBS AND BOTH
MADE IT THROUGH MORE FIT THAN
EVER.
>> COMING UP, ACTOR JUSSIE
SMOLLETT TRIUMPHANT RETURN TO
THE STAGE, YOU DON'T WANT TO
MISS HIS MESSAGE IN OUR VERY
OWN SUPER BOWL CHAMP BRANDON
LONDON SHARES HIGHLIGHTS FROM
HIS TRIP TO SUPER BOWL WEEKEND
IN ATLANTA, EVEN RAMS FANS WANT
TO STICK AROUND FOR THIS.
>>> IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF OF
TIME UNTIL YOUR CHECK ENGINE
LIGHT COMES ON OR WORSE YET
YOUR CAR NEEDS REPAIRS.
THAT COULD MEAN A BIG SURPRISE
AUTO REPAIR BILL, THE REPAIRS
ARE MORE EXPENSIVE THAN EVER, A
NEW ENGINE CAN BE OVER $5000.
A NEW TRANSMISSION OVER $4000,
THAT'S WHY IT'S SO IMPORTANT
YOU CALL CARSHIELD TODAY.
THE NUMBER ONE AUTO PROTECTION
COMPANY IN THE COUNTRY.
>> I LIKE CARSHIELD BECAUSE
THEY WERE RELIABLE, THEY WERE
AFFORDABLE AND THEY WERE
TRUSTWORTHY.
>> I THINK EVERYONE SHOULD HAVE
CARSHIELD, ONCE YOUR
MANUFACTURER'S WARRANTY EXPIRED
THERE IS NO BIG BILLS, YOU NEED
REPAIRS, CARSHIELD WAS THERE
FOR US.
>>> IT'S YOUR TURN TO GET THE
PEACE OF MIND THAT COMES WITH
HAVING CARSHIELD SO YOU CAN
WORRY LESS ABOUT AUTO REPAIRS,
CALL OR GO ONLINE NOW TO GET
CARSHIELD FOR YOURSELF,
FRIENDLY, KNOWLEDGEABLE MONEY-
SAVING REPRESENTATIVES
AVAILABLE 24 HOURS A DAY, IF
YOUR CAR IS 20 YEARS OLD OR
NEWER TELL US THE MAKE AND
MODEL OF YOUR CAR OR TRUCK TO
GET AN INSTANT PLAN QUOTE, IN A
MATTER OF MINUTES YOU COULD BE
COVERED.
>>> I WAS ELATED I HAD
CARSHIELD, IT WAS MORE THAN
HAPPY.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE A CAR THAT'S
BROKEN AND YOU CAN PAY FOR IT
TO BE FIXED THERE'S NOTHING
WORSE.
>>> WHEN YOUR CAR NEEDS REPAIRS
YOU TAKE IT TO YOUR FAVORITE
MECHANIC OR YOUR DEALER IN
CARSHIELD GETS THEM PAID
DIRECTLY.
THAT'S WHY CARSHIELD IS
AMERICA'S NUMBER ONE AUTO
PROTECTION PROVIDER.
>> CARSHIELD IS THE BEST THING
TO TAKE AWAY THE FEAR THAT WHEN
SOMETHING WILL GO WRONG WITH
YOUR CAR, BECAUSE IT WILL,
CARSHIELD WILL BE THERE TO BACK
YOU UP.
>> MY EXPERIENCE WITH CARSHIELD
IS THEY ACTUALLY COME THROUGH
EVERY TIME I NEED THEM.
>>> IF MY CAR BREAKS DOWN I CAN
COUNT ON CARSHIELD TO COVER IT
FOR ME.
CARSHIELD DEFINITELY HAS MY
BACK
>>> NOW'S THE TIME TO MAKE THE
SMART CHOICE AND PROTECT
YOURSELF FROM SKYHIGH AUTO
REPAIR BILLS, CALL NOW FOR FREE
IN THE INSTANT PROTECTION PLAN
QUOTE, IT'S A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE REPAIRS ARE NEEDED AND
ONCE YOUR CAR BREAKS DOWN IT IS
TOO LATE.
>> CALL 1-800-505-9619.
>>> TODAY'S WATCH IN WIND WORD
IS, TROPICAL.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO DBL,  FOR A
FORMER NFL ATHLETE THERE'S NO
BETTER TIME OF THE YEAR THAN
SUPER BOWL WEEK, LUCKY FOR
BRANDON WE SEND THEM TO ATLANTA
TO HANG WITH THE FANS IN HERE
ARE SOME OF HIS HIGHLIGHTS.
>> Reporter: ALL RIGHT DBL
NATION YOUR FAVORITE  SUPER
BOWL CHAMP IN ATLANTA, TAKING
YOU BEHIND THE SCENES FOR THE
SUPER BOWL AND EVENTS BUT IT
STARTS WITH THE NFL EXPERIENCE.
LET'S GO.
NAME 5 PLAYERS ON THE ROSTER
OTHER THAN TOM BRADY AND JULIAN
EDELMAN, GO.
>>> THAT'S REALLY HARD.
>>> DID ANYONE EVER TELL YOU
YOU LOOK LIKE TOM BRADY?
>> SORRY MICHELLE.
>>> IT'S A CURSE.
BUT I LOVE WITH IT.
>>> RAKOWSKI?
>> SHOW ME WHAT YOU DID WHEN
YOU WON THE GAME.
>>> MICHELLE.
>> EDELMAN, TOM BRADY, BILL
BELICHICK
>>> EXCUSE ME SIR YOU
UNDERSTAND YOU ARE AND PATRIOTS
COUNTRY RIGHT NOW?
>> WE ARE STILL CHAMPIONS.
>>> WHO'S YOUR FAVORITE NEW
YORK GIANTS PLAYER OF ALL TIME
AND YOUR STANDING NEXT TO THEM.
>>> YOU ARE MY FAVORITE NEW
YORK GIANTS, ACTUALLY I DON'T
LIKE THE GIANTS, I'M SURE
THEY'RE GREAT, I'M SURE THEY'RE
WONDERFUL PEOPLE.
>> WHO ARE YOU ROOTING FOR,
OFFICE DEPOT?
>> MY CHAMPS ARE NOT IN THE
SUPER BOWL.
>> WHO'S NOT IN THE SUPER BOWL?
STAPLES, WE ARE YOUR TEAM
COLORS?
>> WE ARE FRIENDS NOW.
>> I GUESS WE ARE.
>>> IS THIS HOW WE WILL WATCH
THE GAME SUPER BOWL SUNDAY, ARE
YOU GOING TO THE ACTUAL GAME?
>> GOING TO THE ACTUAL GAME.
>>> YOU UNDERSTAND YOUR THE
ONLY 2 RAMS FANS?
>> WE ARE JUST TAKING LONGER TO
GET HERE.
>>> OH THERE ARE 3 RAMS FANS.
I THINK YOU AND I ARE THE BEST
LOOKING PEOPLE IN THIS CROWD
TODAY.
>>> NOW YOU'VE GOT IT.
>> WHO IS YOUR FAVORITE HOST,
MAYBE HIS NAME IS BRANDON
LONDON?
>> HE IS A CHARMER AND HIS
CHEEKBONES ARE ON.
>>> THEY ARE FORMED PERFECTLY.
>>> YOU ARE GOOD.
>>> THIS IS IN THE TIME.
>>
THIS IS FOR YOU JEFF
>> I CALL IT THE ONE LEG
CHICKEN WING.
THE ONE LEG CHICKEN WING BABY.
>> I THINK THEY ARE CHEERING
FOR ME, I THINK THEY ARE
CHEERING FOR ME.
HEY GUYS I'M HERE.
A GUYS.
>>
COMING UP ON DBL GETTING  90s
NOSTALGIA BIG TIME, COULD
BEVERLY HILLS 90210 BE MAKING A
BIG COMEBACK?
A VOICE MOMENT TO SHINE, ON THE
COURT CAUGHT ON CAMERA, FIND
OUT WHY HIS FIRST CAREER BASKET
WAS EXTRA SPECIAL, COMING UP
NEXT IN HEART THREADS.
>>>
IF A DIRTY CPAP IS MAKING YOU
SICK YOU AREN'T ALONE.
>> I WAS GETTING SINUS
INFECTIONS BECAUSE I WASN'T
CLEANING MY CPAP PROPERLY AND
THAT CONTINUED UNTIL I GOT MY
SOCLEAN.
>> SOCLEAN IS THE WORLD'S FIRST
AUTOMATED CPAP CLEANER AND
SANITIZER, IT CLEANS AND 99.9%
OF ALL CPAP GERMS AND BACTERIA
THAT CAN BUILD IN YOUR MASK,
HOSE AND RESERVOIR.
>> I DON'T NEED TO PUSH A
BUTTON OR ANYTHING, I PUT IT IN
THE CHAMBER AND CLOSE THE LID
AND IT RUNS AUTOMATICALLY.
>> SOCLEAN HAS BEEN A
LIFESAVER.
>> IT WORKS ON ALL POPULAR CPAP
MACHINES AND MASKS, TRY IT RISK-
FREE 30 DAYS, EVEN SHIPPING IS
FREE, CALL ONE 800 418 0640 2
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THIS LIMITED
TIME OFFER.
>> I WOULD RECOMMEND THE
SOCLEAN MACHINE TO ANYONE ELSE.
IT IS THAT GOOD OF A MACHINE,
IT'S MADE THAT BIG OF A
DIFFERENCE IN MY LIFE.
>> TRY SOCLEAN RISK-FREE FOR 30
DAYS, SHIPPING IS FREE, CALL 1-
800-418-0640.
OR GO TO SOCLEAN.COM.
WELCOME BACK TO DBL I AM BEAU
DAVIDSON, TODAY'S HEART THREADS
IS ABOUT  TEAMWORK, WATCHABLE
MIDDLE SCHOOL BEST BALL TEAM
GAVE THEIR MANAGER A GAME HE
WILL NEVER FORGET.  THIS MIDDLE
SCHOOL OR PROVED HIMSELF TO BE
A TRUE TEAM PLAYER.
CHASES AN 8th GRADER WITH DOWN
SYNDROME.
HE IS ALSO THE TEAM MANAGER FOR
HIS SCHOOL'S BASKETBALL TEAM.
ONE NIGHT HE WAS SHOOTING FREE
THROWS WITH HIS TEAM DURING THE
HALF.
HYPING UP THE CROWD AND MAKING
THEM CHEER.
THE OPPOSING TEAMS COACH ONE UP
TO CHASES COACH AND ASKED HIM IF
CHASE COULD PLAY FOR A BIT.
>> ONE THING LED TO ANOTHER, 5
MINUTES INTO THE GAME.
>>> THE WHOLE TIME EVERYONE ON
THE COURT SUPPORTED AND
ENCOURAGED HIM.
>>> THE KIDS WERE AWESOME, THE
REFS WERE AWESOME, THE KIDS
KEPT GRABBING THE REBOUNDS AND
THROWING IT BACK TO HIM SO HE
COULD TRY TO MAKE MORE SHOTS.
>> AND THEN CHEESE MADE A
BASKET AND EVERYONE WAS ON
THEIR FEET.
IT WAS A HUGE MOMENT FOR CHASE
AND THE PEOPLE ROOTING FOR HIM.
>> AT THE END OF THE GAME THERE
WASN'T A DRY EYE IN THE HOUSE.
>> CHASE PICK
>> THAT'S A BEAUTIFUL STORY, I
LOVE SEEING THINGS LIKE THAT,
WE RAN ONE LAST WEEK ABOUT THE
LITTLE GIRL WITH DOWN SYNDROME
WHO GOT THE SCHOLARSHIP FOR
GOLF, I WAS WATCHING A GOLF
TOURNAMENT THIS WEEKEND AND
THEY RAN IT AND I SHOWED MY
WIFE AND SHE STARTED CRYING.
>> JUST WHEN HE SAID I'VE GOT
THIS,  I SAID ALL RIGHT.
>>> BEAUTIFUL.
HERE'S WHAT'S COMING UP NEXT ON
DAILY BLAST LIVE .
>>> EMPIRE AFTER JUSSIE SMOLLETT
, BACK ON STAGE AFTER HIS
ALLEGED HOMOPHOBIC ATTACK.
HIS POWERFUL MESSAGE OF
RESILIENCE.
THEN, GETTING THE OLD GANG BACK
TOGETHER, TORY SPELLING SPILLS
THE BEANS ON THE HIGHLY
ANTICIPATED BEVERLY HILLS 90210
REBOOT AND OUR HOST FACING
THEIR FEARS AND FEBRUARY.
CAN BRANDON LONDON