>>> THIS IS DAILY BLAST LIVE.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT WHAT YOU
ARE TALKING ABOUT.
ALWAYS LIVE, ALWAYS REAL,
ALWAYS UNDETECTABLE.
DESPITE YOU ARE TOTALLY OFF
BASE HERE.
DESPITE LOG ON AND JOIN OUR
LIVE CONVERSATION.
DESPITE I CANNOT BELIEVE I'M
SAYING THIS.
I DO AGREE WITH YOU.
>> DAILY BLAST LIVE STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> WELCOME TO DAILY BLAST
LIVE, IT IS TUESDAY, MAY 7, WE
ARE ALIVE AND WE ARE TALKING
ABOUT WHAT YOU ARE TALKING
ABOUT RIGHT NOW.
I AM HERE WITH TORY, JEFF, AL,
AND I AM SAM.
LET'S GET STARTED.
WE HAVE OUR BRAND-NEW INTERVIEW
WITH POP SENSATION PENTATONIC
JOINING US FROM THEIR FIRST-
EVER WORLD TOUR BUS.
PLUS WE HAVE FASHION SECRETS,
WE ARE TELLING YOU HOW YOU CAN
LOOK YOUR BEST WITHOUT
UPSTAGING THE BRIDE.
COME ON NOW, ADMITTED.
THE STARS BROUGHT THEIR
CRAZIEST MOST OVER-THE-TOP
LOOKS EVER TO THIS YEAR'S MED
GALA.
THE THEME WAS CAMP.
NOTES ON FASHION, AND EVERYONE
WAS EXPECTED TO PULL OUT THE
STOPS.
WHAT IS CAMP?
IT IS DEFINED AS THE LOVE OF
THE UNNATURAL, ARTIFICE, AND
EXAGGERATION.
BASICALLY, EVERYTHING THAT IS
FABULOUS IRONIC OR EXTRA.
LET'S GET TO THE FASHION AND
TITLE THIS YEAR FOR MOST LIVED
GOES TO KATY PERRY WHETHER YOU
HATE IT OR LIKE IT, SHE
DEFINITELY IS HAVING PEOPLE
TALKING.
SHE WORE THIS ILLUMINATED
CHANDELIER LOOK CREATED FOR HER
BY JEREMY, KIM KARDASHIAN
SHOWED OFF HER FIGURE IN A
SKINTIGHT LATEX COURSE ADDRESS,
BLAIR CAME OUT OF RETIREMENT TO
CREATE A LOOK WHICH TOOK GUYS
EIGHT MONTHS TO COMPLETE BY THE
WAY, IT APPEARED TO BE DRIPPING
WET THANKS TO THE CRYSTALS AND
SHIMMERING MATERIAL.
KATIE HOLMES AND JAMIE FOXX
MADE A PUBLIC DEBUT AS A COUPLE
LAST NIGHT WHILE THEY DIDN'T
HIT THE PINK CARPET TOGETHER,
THE COUPLE DID POSE FOR PHOTOS
WITH ONE ANOTHER INSIDE AND
KENDALL AND KYLIE JENNER BROKE
OUT THE FEATHERS, TETHER WORE A
BRIGHT ORANGE FOR SUCH A DOWN,
WHILE KYLIE WENT FOR A MATCHING
WIG.
JANEL MONET EMBRACED WEARABLE
ART WITH THIS CUSTOM LOOK, AND
EVEN WINKED AS SHE CUT DOWN THE
CARPET.
LADY GAGA SERVED AT MULTIPLE
LOOKS, ALL CREATED BY BRANDON
MAXWELL, IT STARTED OFF WITH A
HUGE PINK DRESS, IT TOOK AN
ARMY OF MEN WITH UMBRELLAS, SHE
THEN STRIPPED DOWN TO A BLACK
DRESS FOLLOWED BY A SKINTIGHT
PINK DRESS AND THEN IT ALL
ENDED UP WITH HER POSING IN HER
UNDERWEAR, HERE IT COMES.
YES GIRL.
HUGE PLATFORM SHOES.
SERENA WILLIAMS WORE THIS
STUNNING NEON YELLOW EVER
SOUGHT YOU DOWN WITH PINK NEON
ACCENTS, PAIRING HER LOOK WITH
NEON NIKES.
JENNIFER LOPEZ SPARKLED IN THIS
BEADED VERSE ARCHIE DRESS WITH
A PLUNGING NECKLINE AND FRINGE
DETAILING, SHE WORE A MATCHING
HEADPIECE OF COURSE A-ROD IS A
GOOD ACCESSORY, RIGHT?
>> LIVE ETA EMBRACED THE
RAINBOW WITH THIS VERSE ARCHIE
GOWN, PINK STAR PAM DOWN
RUFFLES, CHECK OUT THE GOLD
AFRO PITS IN HER HAIR, WITH
RAISED FIST LOGOS.
YES.
JARED LETTER, MY FAVORITE, HAD
THE BEST ACCESSORY OF A NICE,
CUSTOM REPLICA, OF HIS HEAD.
HE BROUGHT ALONG ROCKING THIS
GUCCI DRESS.
CASEY MUSGRAVE LOOK LIKE A
BARBIE DOLL IN THIS DRESS.
PAIRING IT WITH A BLOW DRYER
BAG AND CAT EYE SHADES.
CARDY B WON THE AWARD FOR THIS
GOWN, THE 10 FOOT LONG TRAIN IT
NEARLY TOOK OVER THE PINK
CARPET.
SIERRA MIGHT HAVE ONE BEST TEAR
OF THE NIGHT, I THINK SHE ONE
LET'S BE HONEST WITH THIS VERY
EXTRA GORGEOUS AFRO, SHE ALSO
WORE A CUSTOM EMERALD GREEN
CROWN BECAUSE SHE IS A QUEEN
AND SUNDAY I HAD A FAIRLY --
FAIRYTALE MOMENT TRANSFORMING
INTO CINDERELLA IN THIS TOMMY
HILFIGER BALLGOWN WITH A SKIRT
THAT LIT UP.
YES YES YES.
>> YOU DRINK SOME WATER.
WE WILL TALK.
>> I ACTUALLY LOOKED AT JEFF
MIDWAY AND HER EYES WERE CLOSED.
>> I WAS OUT, I WAS SPEAKING
ABOUT CHEESE AND CRACKERS AND
WHAT I WILL DO TONIGHT.
>> WHAT I WAS THINKING IS THIS
COFFEE IS BETTER, I SHOULD
THINK ABOUT A DIFFERENT KIND OF
COFFEE.
>> I GUESS I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO
REALLY APPRECIATES THE LOOK AS
ART.
>> THEY'RE THERE TO ENTERTAIN
US.
LIKE SOMEBODY HAS TO SHAKE IT
UP A BIT, WE CAN'T ALL WEAR
KHAKIS AND POLO SHIRTS.
SOMEBODY'S GOT TO SHAKE IT UP
AND PUSH THE ENVELOPE.
>> I'M FOR UNIVERSAL UNIFORMS
EVERY DAY.
>> STAR TREK?
>> YESTERDAY
>> BORING.
>> I WEAR THE SAME THING TO
WORK EVERY DAY, THAT'S FINE FOR
ME.
DESPITE I DO THE SAME THING.
>> TORY, DID YOU HAVE A
FAVORITE EVEN IF YOU WERE BORED
BY IT?
>> I DID HAVE A FAVORITE.
EZRA MILLER  ABSOLUTELY NAILED
CAMP, AND THIS IS A GUY WHO IS
GENDER FLUID AND HE USED
PROSTHETICS, YOU REALLY GOT
>> THOSE WEREN'T REALIZE?
>> NOW, I DON'T KNOW WHY I SAID
BUT IT'S ABOUT THE ARTIFICE AND
EXAGGERATION OF THE LIKE TO THE
GENDER FLUIDITY, THAT WAS ALL
OVER THE RED CARPET.
PINK CARPET, EXCUSE ME.
>> I LOVE THAT TOO.
>> I'M GOING TO NOD MY HEAD AND
PRETEND I KNOW WHAT ARTIFICE
MEANS.
>> ARTIFICIAL MISS.
CAMP IS VERY CATCHY AND FAKE
AND OVERDONE.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> CAMPY.
>> WE DO CALL YOU AL FASHION,
YOU HAD TO HAVE A FAVORITE?
>> MY BOY NICK JONAS.
>> YOUR BOY?
>> WE GO WAY BACK.
>> HE LOOKS LIKE A WAITER AT
THE CHEESECAKE FACTORY DOESN'T
HE?
>> IN DUBAI.
THE DUBAI CHEESECAKE FACTORY.
YOU NAILED IT.
JEFF, DO YOU HAVE A FAVORITE?
>> I KNOW EVERYONE HATES THE
GENDERS I SHOULD SAY, CHECK
THEM OUT BUT I LIKE HOW THEY
DIDN'T WALK WITH THEIR DATES
DOWN THE CARPET.
>> THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
>> LISTEN.
I THINK ALL THE WORK THESE
FASHION DESIGNERS PUT INTO
THESE OUTFITS, I REALLY WANT TO
GIVE THEM SOME CREDIT.
>> WHO WAS YOUR FAVORITE?
>> JANEL MONET.
>> THAT DRESS IS ART, YOU GUYS.
AGAIN WITH THE GENDER FLUIDITY,
I THINK THAT JARED LETTER, WITH
THAT GORGEOUS RED DOWN, AND WHO
DOESN'T LOVE A SEVERED HEAD AS
A PURSE.
>> I DON'T THINK ANYONE KNOWS
HE'S WEARING A GOWN, I THINK
THAT'S THE WAY YOU DO IT IS YOU
JUST CARRY HUNDRED I DIDN'T
REALIZE IT WAS A DOWN UNTIL YOU
SAID SOMETHING.
>> THAT WAS A PURSE?
>> OR AN ACCESSORY BUT HE HELD
IT LIKE A PURSE.
>> HE SURE DID.
>> I'M ALL FOR IT.
>> WHAT IF MARK SHOWED UP WITH
A PURSE OF YOUR HEAD?
>> FASHION.
>> EXACTLY.
>> LET'S GET TO THIS NEXT STORY.
AN UPDATE TO THE COLLEGE
ADMISSION SCANDAL.
LORI LOCKLIN'S DEFENSE MIGHT
HAVE GOTTEN A BOOST THANKS TO
THE UNIVERSITY OF SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA'S CREW TEAM.
REPORTING THIS OUT FOR THE TEAM
POSTING ALL OVER CAMPUS.
YOU CAN SEE IT SAYS NO
EXPERIENCE NO PROBLEM, SOME SAY
THE POSTER COULD HELP THE
DEFENSE.
HER DAUGHTER'S LACK OF
EXPERIENCE, THE TEAM DOESN'T
REQUIRE EXPERIENCE TO JOIN,
LORI OF COURSE IS ACCUSED OF
PAYING BRIBES TO TOSS PASS HER
OFF AS ATHLETIC RECRUITS IN
ORDER TO GET THEM INTO USC.
NOW, TORY, I KNOW YOU ARE OUR
LEGAL EAGLE.
THIS MAKES MY BLOOD BOIL,
BECAUSE IF LORI LOCKLIN IS
GOING TO USE THIS AS A DEFENSE,
SHE IS SUGGESTING THAT ALL OF
US ARE STUPID.
SHE IS SUGGESTING THAT
EVERYBODY OUT THERE WHO HAS
WORKED HARD TO GET INTO A
UNIVERSITY, WHETHER YOU ARE AN
ASSET ATHLETE, WHETHER YOU ARE
A SCHOLAR, AGAIN, IS A STUPID.
COULD THIS WORK FOR HER?
>> IT COULD GO BOTH WAYS.
IT COULD BACKFIRE COMPLETELY,
BECAUSE IT IS SO OBVIOUS.
WE HAVE HER ON TAPE BEING LIKE
TAKE A PICTURE OF THEM AND SEND
IT IN.
WE KNOW THE REAL THING.
SHE INSULTED SO MANY PEOPLE
WHEN PLEADING NOT GUILTY.
THAT'S WHERE SHE MADE A MISTAKE
AS WE HAVE TALKED ABOUT BEFORE.
IT ONLY TAKES ONE PERSON TO BE
LIKE, MAYBE SHE DID NOT KNOW,
THOUGH.
SO, THEY ARE USING THE LOOPHOLE
DEFENSE, IT'S A HAIL MARY, BUT
IT HAS WORKED BEFORE.
ALL SHE WANTS TO DO IS AVOID
PRISON TIME.
>> I THINK SHE'S GOING TO DO
THAT.
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
LISTEN.
SHE IS NOT CALLING US STUPID.
OUR JUDICIAL SYSTEM IS CALLING
US STUPID.
THE PEOPLE WHO DEFEND HER ARE
CALLING US STUPID BECAUSE IF
SHE GETS OFF IT JUST PROVES
THAT OUR SYSTEM DOES NOT WORK.
THAT'S WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
>> YOU ARE RIGHT.
YOU CAN BUY YOUR WAY OUT OF
JAIL.
>> MANY WOULD ARGUE OUR SYSTEM
WORKS IN THE OPPOSITE WAY
BECAUSE YOU DO HAVE WOMEN OF
COLOR WHO ARE LOCKED OUT FOR
SENDING YOUR KID TO A PUBLIC
SCHOOL IN A DIFFERENT ZIP CODE.
>> YES.
>> AL, DOES THE JUDICIAL SYSTEM
WORK OR DOES IT NOT WORK,
DEPENDING ON HOW YOU LOOK AT IT
INSIDE THAT LENS?
>> I THINK IT IS WORKING
PERFECTLY.
>> IT CATERS TO THE RICH.
IF YOU ARE RICH, YOU DON'T SEE
JAIL AS A DETERRENT.
ANYBODY THAT HAS MONEY, YOU CAN
GET A GOOD ATTORNEY, THEY COST
DIFFERENT AMOUNTS OF MONEY SOME
OF THEM FREE, SOME WILL SAY
TAKE THE DEAL.
A GREAT LAWYER WILL GO THROUGH
EVERYTHING.
ALL THEY NEED IS ONE THING, AND
THAT IS WHY YOU PAY THAT MONEY.
IF YOU HAVE MONEY, YOU'RE GOING
TO GET THAT LAWYER AND THEY
WILL GET YOU OFF.
THAT IS WHY JEFF FEELS LIKE
THAT BECAUSE IT IS TRUE.
>> SHAME ON HER AND SHAME ON
THE JUDICIAL SYSTEM.
WE NEED REFORM AND WE NEED
REFORM NOW.
DAILY BLAST LIVE IS LIVE, WE
BRING YOU BREAKING NEWS AS IT
HAPPENS, COMING UP, A CAPPELLA
NEVER SOUNDED SO GOOD.
THE BAND PENTATONIC TAKES TIME
TO CHAT WITH US IN THE MIDDLE
OF THEIR FIRST-EVER WORLD TOUR.
THEN, AN EYE-OPENING STUDY ALL
ABOUT SUNSCREEN.
THE SURPRISING NEW FINDINGS
THAT MIGHT MAKE YOU RETHINK THE
KIND OF SUNBLOCK YOU USE, YOU
THE VIEWER ARE OUR FIFTH
HOUSTON WE WANT YOUR TAKE ON
THIS CONTROVERSIAL STORY.
A BARTENDER IS IN TROUBLE AFTER
PROSECUTORS SAY SHE OVERSERVED
A MAN RIGHT BEFORE GOING ON A
SHOOTING RAMPAGE.
SHOULD SHE BE CHARGED WITH THE
CRIME, SENDING COMMENTS RIGHT
NOW, WE WILL READ THEM LIVE
NEXT.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
IT IS TIME FOR FIFTH POST, WHEN
WE TALK ABOUT WHAT YOU ARE
TALKING ABOUT, A TEXAS
BARTENDER HAS BEEN ARRESTED AND
CHARGED FOR OVER SERVING A MAN
THE NIGHT HE SHOT AND KILLED
EIGHT PEOPLE.
LINDSAY GLASS IS ACCUSED OF
VIOLATING A STATE LAW BY
SELLING ALCOHOL TO AN
INTOXICATED OR INSANE PERSON.
POLICE SAY SHE SHOULD HAVE
KNOWN TO STOP SERVING THE MAN
BECAUSE HE APPEARED DRUNK AND
ARMED.
TURNED OUT, HIS BLOOD-ALCOHOL
LEVEL WAS MORE THAN FOUR TIMES
THE LEGAL LIMIT.
AFTER LEAVING THE BAR, THE MAN
KILLED HIS ESTRANGED WIFE AND
SEVEN OTHERS BEFORE DYING IN A
POLICE SHOOTOUT.
THE BARTENDER NOW FACES UP TO A
YEAR IN PRISON, A FINE OF $500
OR BEST, SHOULD SHE BE CHARGED
WITH A CRIME.
NOW, SHE WOULDN'T BE CHARGED
FOR MURDER, THIS WOULD BE A
MISDEMEANOR, SO TO SPEAK AT
THIS POINT TO CLARIFY THAT
>> I THINK THE BARTENDER IS
RESPONSIBLE FOR KEEPING PATRONS
FROM BECOMING UNREASONABLY
INTOXICATED.
BUT ONLY THE SHOOTER IS
RESPONSIBLE FOR MURDER.
BOBBY, GREAT TAKE.
YOU USE THE WORD THERE
UNREASONABLY INTOXICATED.
FOUR TIMES THE LEGAL LIMIT
MEANS YOU PROBABLY CAN'T STAND
UP.
THE FACT THAT THIS MAN WAS
ARMED, TO THE POINT WHERE SHE
WAS AWARE OF IT, I THINK SHE
SHOULD BE IMPLICATED IN SOME
WAY, MY WHOLE THING, I'M NOT
THROWING PEOPLE IN JAIL, THE
SHOULD BE USED TO TEACH OTHER
PEOPLE YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE TO
TEACH PEOPLE NOT TO SERVE DRUNK
PEOPLE WITH GUNS, BUT SOME
PEOPLE GOT TO LEARN THEIR
LESSON I GUESS.
>> PATTY FROM FACEBOOK SAYS
BARS ARE JUST OUT TO MAKE
MONEY, THEY DON'T CARE ABOUT
THE DANGERS OF ALCOHOL THIS
NEEDS TO CHANGE.
>> SAM YOU WERE A BARTENDER,
THERE ARE STRICT LAWS ABOUT
SERVING PEOPLE THAT YOU CAN
REASONABLY SEE OUR OVERSERVED.
>> THEY MAKE AN EXAMPLE OUT OF
YOU.
IN LOS ANGELES IT'S A
CORPORATION CALLED ABC, THEY
TRAIN YOU AND LET YOU KNOW
ABOUT RED FLAGS.
GOD FORBID YOU EVER SERVE
SOMEONE, BOTH JEFF AND I HAVE
CUT MANY PEOPLE OFF.
WE HAVE BOTH SEEN PEOPLE, OUR
COLLEAGUES, DRAGGED OUT OF THAT
BAR IN HANDCUFFS, BECAUSE OF A
DUI, YOU COULD KILL SOMEONE YOU
COULD KILL YOURSELF.
>> THOUGHT OUT THE BACK DOOR
THEY MAKE SURE THEY SEE THEM AT
THE FRONT DOOR, IT IS A BIG
DEAL.
>> ALCOHOL IS A DRUG.
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD BE
LIABLE.
IF YOU ARE A GUN MAKER SELLING
TO AN UNDERAGE PERSON BY
MISTAKE YOU ARE LIABLE, IF THEY
SHOOT SOMEONE YOU ARE ALSO
LIABLE.
SHE BROKE THE LAW.
BUT I DO WANT TO SET THIS UP
THOUGH, WE TALK ABOUT THIS
STORY WE SET UP FOR A MINUTE,
WE DON'T KNOW IF THIS GUY WAS
COMING UP TO THE BAR, WE DON'T
KNOW WHAT WAS GOING ON.
OBVIOUSLY I'VE SEEN SOMEONE
FALL OUT OF THE CHAIR, I KNOW
TO CUT THEM OFF.
IF THEY ARE ALL OVER THE PLACE,
I DON'T KNOW.
IN SPITE OF THE DRINKING AND
THE BACK ROOM?
>> DID A DRINK BEFORE THEY
CAME?
THERE'S A LOT THAT GOES INTO
THIS WEEKEND JUST TO SPECULATE
ON WHAT THE BARTENDER DID OR
DID NOT SEE.
MARCUS FROM PITTSBURGH SAYS HOW
COULD THE BARTENDER HAVE KNOWN
WHAT THIS GUY WAS GOING TO DO
AFTER LEAVING.
HOLD PEOPLE ACCOUNTABLE FOR
THEIR OWN ACTIONS.
MARCUS I LOVE YOU FOR SAYING
THAT.
ACCOUNTABILITY.
I THINK A WORD THAT HAS BEEN
ERASED FROM THE DICTIONARY.
BE ACCOUNTABLE FOR YOUR OWN
ACTIONS, NOT BECAUSE YOUR FIFTH
GRADE TEACHER GAVE YOU AN AND
CALLED YOU A NAME, THAT IS WHY
YOU WENT AND SHOT UP EVERYBODY,
NOT BECAUSE THE BARTENDER OVER
SURETY  OVERSERVED YOU, HOLD
THIS MAN ACCOUNTABLE.
DOES THIS LADY NEED TO DO HER
JOB DEPENDING ON THE
CIRCUMSTANCES?
MAYBE.
THIS MAN IS ACCOUNTABLE, NOT
ANYBODY ELSE.
HE'S THE ONE WHO KILLED EIGHT
PEOPLE, LET'S NOT FORGET THAT
THEIR DISPATCH THANKS GREAT
TAKES EVERYBODY THANK YOU FOR
WRITING APPEARED COMING UP, EAT
BETTER SLEEP BETTER.
I AM ALREADY SOLD.
WE HAVE THE TOP FOLDS THAT A
NUTRITIONIST SAYS WILL HELP YOU
GET A GOOD NIGHTS REST, AND POP
SENSATION PENT UP PENTATONIC
JOINS US FOR THE FIRST TIME,
FIND OUT WHY THEIR UNIQUE A
CAPPELLA STYLE IS WOWING
AUDIENCES EVERYWHERE WHEN WE
COME BACK.
>> ♪ GOODBYE EVERYBODY, I'VE
GOT TO GO.
♪
>> ♪ GOT TO LEAVE YOU ALL
BEHIND.
>> WHAT YOU JUST HEARD INVOLVED
NO INSTRUMENTS.
ONLY FIVE VOICES, A CAPPELLA
BAND PENTATONIC JUST KICKED OFF
THEIR FIRST WORLD TOUR.
I CAUGHT UP WITH THREE OF THE
BANDS FIVE MEMBERS IN TODAY'S
CHATTING WITH THE STARS.
>> Reporter: SCOTT MITCH AND
KEVIN, WELCOME TO DAILY BLAST
LIVE.
PENTATONIC'S ARE ABOUT TO KICK
OFF A WORLD TOUR, BUT I WOULD
LIKE TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT YOUR
EARLY DAYS.
YOU GUYS MADE YOUR MARK
COVERING POPULAR SONGS ON
YOUTUBE.
IS THERE A SONG OR ARTIST YOU
HAVE NOT COVERED YET, BUT YOU
HAVE YOUR SIGHTS SET ON?
>> WE HAVEN'T REALLY DONE A
TAYLOR SWIFT SONG.
>> YEAH.
WE COULD DO THE NEW ONE.
EXACTLY.
THAT WOULD BE FUN.
>> YOU GUYS KEEP TALKING WORLD
TOUR.
YET THERE ARE STILL SOME
CRITICS WHO SAY YOU GUYS ARE
JUST A COVER BAND.
HOW DO YOU RESPOND TO THAT
CRITICISM?
>> IT DOESN'T REALLY BOTHER US.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, WE TAKE
SONGS WE LOVE AND DO THEM IN A
WAY THAT ONLY WE CAN DO THEM
WHICH IS A VERY SPECIAL ABILITY
WE HAVE CREATED OVER THE PAST
FEW YEARS AND IT'S BEEN REALLY
FUN GETTING INTO A ORIGINAL
MUSIC, IT'S A JOURNEY AND WE
HOPE WE CONTINUE TO GROW.
>> I WANT TO PLAY A RAPIDFIRE
QUESTION GAME WITH YOU ALL.
I'M CALLING IT ANSWERS WITH
PENTATONIC.
ARE YOU READY?
FIRST ONE, WHO IN THE BAND IS
ALWAYS LATE TO REHEARSAL?
>> ME.
I'M ALWAYS LIKE FIVE MINUTES
LATE.
>> WHO IS THE MOM OF THE GROUP?
>> COUNTER I THINK.
>> THAT'S NICE.
>> IS THE MOST ORGANIZED.
>> THANK YOU, I APPRECIATE IT.
>> WHO CALLS THEM ON THE MOST?
>> YOU DO.
>> GOOD SON AWARD.
WHO IS ALWAYS TAKING CELL FEES?
>> KIRSTEN.
>> WHO IS ALWAYS SNACKING?
>> SNACKING?
YOU OR ME.
>> PROBABLY SCOTT.
>>> AND THE LAST ONE, AS A
GROUP WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE
SONG TO PERFORM?
>> BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY.
>> YEAH, THAT'S A CROWD
PLEASER.
>> SINCE THAT IS YOUR FAVORITE,
DO YOU MIND GIVING ME A LITTLE
SNIPPET?
>> OH MY GOSH, IT'S HARD ENOUGH
WITH FIVE PEOPLE REALLY HAVE
THREE PEOPLE WITH US RIGHT NOW.
>> I WOULD OFFER MY SERVICES
BUT, BELIEVE ME, YOUR EARS
WOULD BE DAMAGED FOR LIFE.
>> THANK YOU GUYS, SCOTT KEVIN
AND MITCH, THREE OF THE FIVE
VOICES OF PENTATONIC'S.
ON A WORLD TOUR CHECK THESE
GUYS OUT IN A CITY NEAR YOU YOU
WILL NOT REGRET IT.
THANKS GUYS YOU'VE BEEN
AWESOME.
>> THANK YOU, YOU TOO.
>> WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>> PROMOTIONAL CONSIDERATION
IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY:
You've tried so many
moisturizers...
but one blows them all
out of the water.
Hydro Boost with hyaluronic acid
to plump skin cells
so it bounces back...
Neutrogena®
And try our hydrating makeup.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO DBL.
MAKING THE RIGHT FOOD CHOICES
CAN BE TOUGH, TORY MEETS UP
WITH A NUTRITIONIST TO LEARN
ABOUT FOODS THAT WILL HELP YOU
SLEEP BETTER, TAKE A LOOK.
>> HI GUYS WE ARE HERE WITH
SARAH PETER, HOLISTIC
NUTRITIONIST AT FAMILY
NUTRITION SERVICES SHE IS HERE
TO TELL US HOW FOOD CAN AFFECT
YOUR SLEEP.
I KNOW.
TALK TO ME ABOUT HOW SLEEP AND
EATING GO TOGETHER, BECAUSE I
NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT THAT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WHO HASN'T HAD TROUBLE SLEEPING
AT ONE POINT OR ANOTHER.
I KNOW I HAVE.
>> WHAT ARE SPECIFIC FOODS?
>> THERE ARE FOODS RICH IN
AMINO ACID CALLED CALLED
TRYPTOPHAN.
THE FIRST ONE IS TURKEY.
>> RIGHT, THAT'S WHAT EVERYONE
IS SO SLEEPY AND THANKS GIVING.
>> NUTS ARE ACCESSIBLE SOURCE
OF TRYPTOPHAN.
JUST EATING A BIT A DAY CAN
BOOST YOUR TRYPTOPHAN LEVELS
POINT
>> YOU BE NUTS NOT TO DO IT.
>> TOTALLY NUTS.
>> WHAT ELSE OTHER THAN NUTS?
>> MY FAVORITE ONE OF ALL IS
CHERRIES.
CHERRIES WHEN THEY CONTAIN
MELATONIN BUT ACTUALLY JUST HOW
TO CONTRIBUTE TO YOUR BODIES ON
PRODUCTION OF MELATONIN.
THIS IS SLEEP HORMONE IS ONE OF
THE HORMONES THAT REGULATES OUR
CIRCADIAN RHYTHM.
CHERRIES, NUTS, WHAT ELSE?
>> FISH.
ACTUALLY IS A SLEEP REMEDY, NOT
THOUGHT OF BUT IT SHOULD BE
BECAUSE IT HAS A VERY HIGH
LEVEL OF VITAMIN B6.
>> B6 HELPS YOU SLEEP?
>> VITAMIN B6 IS ACTUALLY
IMPORTANT FOR THAT CONVERSION
OF TRYPTOPHAN TO SEROTONIN.
>> I SEE POINT
>> WE ARE TALKING ABOUT NUTS,
AMINO ACIDS IN OUR BODIES USE
TO CONVERT TO SEROTONIN BUT IF
YOU ARE LOW IN B6 THAT
CONVERSION DOESN'T IT LAYS
QUITE AS NATURALLY.
>> I WANT TO THANK SARAH PETER
NOW FOR DEALING WITH ME FIRST
OFFENSE FOR TEACHING US
ACCESSIBLE THINGS TO DO RIGHT
NOW AT THE GROCERY STORE TO
HELP YOUR OWN BODY NATURALLY
GET TO SLEEP.
>> I GUESS I NEED TO STOCK UP ON
CHERRIES.
>> YOU BEEN HAVING TROUBLE SHE
ALSO MENTIONED TO ME YOGURT.
YOU MAKE A SMOOTHIE AND INCLUDE
ALL OF THIS, YOGA CHERRIES
WALNUTS, YOU CAN SORT OF MAKE A
SLEEPY TIME SMOOTHIE.
SO IF YOU THINK MAY BE RIGHT
WHEN YOU ARE FEELING IT YOU CAN
GET IN THE MOOD TO SLEEP.
>> HERE'S WHAT'S COMING UP NEXT.
>>> ENTERTAINMENT ICONS TAKE
FASHION TO AN OUTRAGEOUS NEW
LEVEL AT THE ANNUAL MEDI-CAL IN
NEW YORK.
>>> WHO CAME DRESSED AS A BIRD?
>>> THEN, SUNSCREEN DANGER
EXPOSED, THE NEW FDA STUDY THAT
MIGHT MAKE YOU THINK TWICE
BEFORE SLATHERING SUNBLOCK ON
THIS SUMMER.
WEDDING SERIES CONTINUES WITH
THE MOST FLATTERING LOOKS FOR
GUESTS.
WE'VE GOT SOMETHING FOR
EVERYONE WHEN WE COME BACK.
Get the deals now during
the great American tent sale
at Sears.
SAVE up to 50% off
summer fashions and sandals
for the family
including kids' swimwear
starting at $8.
AND up to 40% off appliances
including this Kenmore
French door refrigerator
for twelve ninety-nine
ninety-nine.
PLUS, you get $300 CASHBACK
in points
to spend anywhere in the store
over twenty weeks.
Start your shopping during
the great American tent sale
in store or at sears.com
to start making
your summer moments matter.