>>> THIS IS "DAILY BLAST LIVE."
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>> EVERYBODY IS TALKING ABOUT
THIS.
>> ALWAYS LIVE, ALWAYS REAL,
ALWAYS UNPREDICTABLE.
>> YOU ARE TOTALLY OFF BASE
HERE.
>> LOG ON AND JOIN OUR LIVE
CONVERSATION.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M SAYING
THIS.
I DO AGREE WITH YOU.
>> "DBL" STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> THREE, TWO --
>> WELCOME TO "DBL."
IT'S WEDNESDAY, FEBRUARY 13th.
WE ARE LIVE AND WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT.
I'M HERE WITH TORY, AL, JEFF
AND I'M SAM.
WE HAVE DR. DREW.
YOU'RE NOT ONLY A FRIEND BUT MY
MENTOR.
>> THERE'S A REASON WE WORK
WITH YOU.
YOU'RE GOOD.
>> THAT MEANS SO MUCH TO ME.
>> EMERGENCY FALLOUT.
>> THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE,
DR. DREW.
WE BEGIN WITH A STORY WE'VE
BEEN TRACKING.
HE JUSSIE'S REPS SAID CHICAGO
PD FIND HIS STORY CONSISTENT AND
CREDIBLE.
THIS COME HAS DAY AFTER A
SPOKESPERSON SAID THE KNOWN
RECORDS DO NOT MEET THE BURDEN
FOR A CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION
HAS THEY WERE LIMITED AND
HEAVILY REACTED.
JUSSIE'S REPS CLAIM INFORMATION
WAS REMOVED TO PROVENT OTHERS
WHO HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THE
ATTACK.
CHECK OUT THIS TEASER.
>> AT ANY POINT DURING THE
ATTACK DID YOU FEAR FOR YOUR
ATTACK?
>> YOU HAVE BEEN FOLLOWING IT.
WHAT WOULD YOU SAY ABOUT THE
NARRATIVE?
>> IT'S NOT OUR JOB TO CREATE A
NARRATIVE.
IF HE HAS OVERSTATED IT, I'M
STILL WORRIED.
SO ALL OF US SIT BACK.
IT'S NOT OUR BUSINESS.
>> TORY, YOU HAVE A STRONG
TAKE.
>> INNOCENT UNTIL PROVEN
GUILTY.
IF IT'S NOT TRUE, DR. DREW IS
RIGHT, THERE MAY BE SOMETHING
ELSE WRONG.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN ANYTHING.
I MEAN TOM BRADY DIDN'T GIVE UP
HIS PHONE WHEN IT'S DEFLATE-
GATE AND WE'RE JUMPING ON THIS
GUY.
>> ANYTHING WE GET FROM THE
STORY WILL PUSH THE NARRATIVE.
THERE'S MONEY TO BE MADE FROM
DIVISION.
UNFORTUNATELY, IT'S THE WORLD
WE LIVE IN.
THE CONSPIRACY THEORISTS SAY
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE IS A HOAX,
PARKLAND, SANDY HOOK, PIZZA
GATE.
EVERYBODY, UNFORTUNATELY HAS A
FINANCIAL INTEREST.
I GUARANTEE A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE
NOT FANS OF HIS AND DO CARE
ABOUT HIS PHYSICAL WELL-BEING.
THEY JUST SEE THE KID AS A WAY
IT FURTHER THEIR AGENDA.
>> I WOULD ENCOURAGE PEOPLE IF
YOU THINK THERE ARE HOLES IN
HIS STORY, WHICH I DON'T, WAIT
FOR THE INTERVIEW.
>> WE WILL BE COVERING THE
INTERVIEW TOMORROW.
>> THE MEDIA CREATES NARRATIVE.
THOSE HEADLINES, THAT'S FOR THE
GOOD OF THE NARRATIVE.
THEY WANT IT MAKE MONEY.
>> BE AN INDIVIDUAL THINKER AND
CHIME IN "DBL" NATION.
WE FINALLY HAVE GOOD NEWS
COMING OUT OF WASHINGTON, D.C.
MANY.
>>WE ARE TWO DAYS AWAY FROM A
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
CONGRESSIONAL LEADERS CAME UP
WITH A TENTATIVE DEAL.
SOURCES SAY HE IS EXPECTED TO
SIGN IT.
IN THE MEANTIME TED CRUZ IS
BACKING ANOTHER PLAN.
CRUZ SAID WE SHOULD USE THE
MONEY U.S. PROSECUTORS ARE
SEEKING FROM NOW CONVICTED EL
CHAPO.
THEY'RE SEEKING $14 BILLION IN
PROFLTS AND CRUZ SAID THAT
MONEY SHOULD GO TOWARD SECURITY
BORDER.
>>> WELL, WE HAVE A NEW TO DOG.
MEET KING THE FOX TERRIER.
I CALLED IT THE BEST IN SHOW
LAMPS NIGHT AT THE WESTMINSTER
DOG SHOW.
COMPETITION WAS ROUGH.
THE FOX TERRIER WON THE TOP
PRIZE.
THIS MARKS THE 15th TIME THAT
BREED HAS COME OUT ON TOP.
THE LONG HAIRED DACHSHUND DID
NOT WIN.
AND THE SKIPPER WHO WON THE
NONSPORTING GROUP WAS
DISQUALIFIED.
>> SCANDAL.
>> DUE TO A CONFLICT OF
INTEREST.
>> I THOUGHT I WAS BACK IN
FRANCE.
>> AND THIS SUSSEX SPANIEL
NAMED BEAN WHO WON THE SPORTING
GROUP AND MEET WILMA THE BOXER,
BUT IT WASN'T JUST US HUMANS.
CHECK OUT ALL THESE DOGS WHO
REALLY GOT INTO THE ACTION.
TORY, I KNOW, FIRST OF ALL,
SCANDAL.
>> BIG SCANDAL.
>> SKIPPER KEY WAS IN IT.
THEY SHOOK HANDS WITH THE JUDGE
AND SAID I NEED YOU TO LEAVE.
THAT IS SCANDAL, AM I RIGHT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> BECAUSE THE JUDGE WAS A CO-
OWNER OF SAID DOG.
>> SHOULDN'T THAT BE ILL LOCAL?
>> THIS WAS.
HE DID A NICE LAUGH AND WALKED.
>> THE BEARDED GUY THAT LOOKS
LIKE SHERLOCKS, HE LOOKS LIKE A
DOG.
AT SOME POINT THAT DOG WAS ON.
HE STOOD LIKE THIS AND HE, THE
CROWD.
>> CAN I GET A ONE IS THE ON
TORY WHEN SHE DOES THAT.
THIS IS THE DACHSHUND, ONE SHOT
ON TORY.
>> PLEASE DON'T PUT ME IN IT.
>> IT WAS MADISON SQUARE
GARDEN, THANK YOU.
>> LOOK AT JEFF.
>> WE COVERED THIS STORY MORE
THAN THE SUPER BOWL.
>> CAN ANYONE EXPLAIN WHY I
WATCH IT EVERY YEAR AFTER THE
MACY'S THANKSGIVING DAY PARADE.
>> THEY SHOULD HAVE RESCUE DOGS
ONLY.
>> THEY CALL IT THE ONE PEOPLE
DON'T WASH EYE LIKE THE
BEAUTIFUL DOGS.
COME ON.
IT DOESN'T MOON YOU HAVE TO BUY
ONE.
>> COMING UP ON "DBL," DR. DREW
ANSWERS YOUR BURNING QUESTIONS
ABOUT LOVE AND RELATIONSHIP AND
WHY YOU SHOULDN'T MESS WITH
SINGER MIRANDA LAMBERT.
PLUS, ACTOR ANSON WILSON TELLS
US ABOUT HAPPY DAYS AND'S
SQUIRE MAGAZINE IS IN THE
CENTER OF A FIRE STORM OVER
THIS COVER.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHY A LITTLE
LATER.
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "DBL."
I WOULD HAVE A SPECIAL GUEST.
YOU KNOW HIM FROM LOVE LINE AND
CELEBRITY -- IT'S DR. DREW
PINSKY.
THIS IS IMPORTANT.
A LOT OF OUR VIEWERS AT HOME,
YOU LOVE HIS ADVICE ON
ADDICTION AND RELATIONSHIPS BUT
TODAY WE'RE FOCUSING ON
RELATIONSHIPS AND ASKED VIEWERS
TO SEND IN FOR A SEGMENT WE'RE
CALLING DEAR DR. DREW DBL.
>> ONE PERSON MY BEDROOM LIFE
WITH MY GIRLFRIEND  SUCKS.
THREE TIME AS WEEK IF I'M
LUCKY.
>> THREE TIMES A WEEK ABOVE
AVERAGE BY THE WAY.
>> THAT'S ABOVE AVERAGE?
YES.
>> AVERAGE IN A LONG TERM
RELATIONSHIP.
>> WHAT ABOUT A NEW
>> SOME PEOPLE ARE AT THAT
RATE.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
PEOPLE HAVE TO REACH A
COMPROMISE.
>> MORNING AND NIGHT, JEFF.
>> I LOVE SLEEP.
>> IT'S ABOUT COMPROMISING.
YOU HAVE TO TELL HER THIS IS
NOT YOUR RATE AND YOU HAVE TO
STEP IT UP.
ONE OF THE THINGS I SEE
COMMONLY IN YOUNG COUPLES WHEN
A FEMALE SEXUAL DESIRE DOES NOT
MATCH A MAN SHE MAY BE ON A
HIGH PROJEST TER PRONE BIRTH
CONTROL.
SO TAKE A LOOK AT THE BIRTH
THE PROGESTERONE.
>> THIS GUY.
HE'S LIKE A FOUNTAIN OF
KNOWLEDGE.
>> ELLIE SAYS MY HUSBAND
GAMBLES COMPULSIVELY AND
FREQUENTS GENTLEMEN'S CLUBS.
WE ARE DROWNING IN DEBT.
SHOULD I WALK OUT.
>> ELLIE MAE, LIKE FROM THE
BEVERLY HILLBILLIES?
THIS IS A TRAGEDY AND THIS IS A
GREAT EXAMPLE OF HOW REAL
GAMBLING ADDICTION DESTROYS
LIFE.
THERE COULD BE SEXUAL
ADDICTION.
GO TO AL-ANON.
THERE'S SPECIFIC ONES FOR
GAMBLING AND SEX ACTS BUT AL-
ANONIS EASY TO FIND.
HE GETS TREATMENT OR YOU LEAVE.
>> ANOTHER WE BOTH PEOPLE
STRONGLY.
SHE'S NOT READY FOR A
RELATIONSHIP.
WE CAN'T STOP SEEING EACH
OTHER.
IT FEELS LIKE A REBOUND.
>> I HAVE TO FINISH, DOES HE GO
TO GA, GAMBLING'S ANONYMOUS.
OR SEX ACTS AEN IN ANONYMOUS.
WHEN SOMEONE IS GOING THROUGH A
DIVORCE YOU'RE MORE OF A LIFE
PRESERVER WHEN SOMEONE'S GOING
THROUGH A HORRIBLE CRISIS.
I WOULD NEED A WHOLE LOT MORE
INFORMATION.
>> COULD IT WORK OUT?
>> I COULD BUT I HAVE BAD
FEELINGS ABOUT THIS.
>> INTERESTING.
>> I JUST READ RUTH.
>> TREVOR IN TAMPA SAID MY
GIRLFRIEND GETS MAD AT ME FOR
NOT POSTING PICTURES OF US ON
SOCIAL MEDIA.
I LIKE TO POST ABOUT MY
HOBBIES, SHE THINKS I'M HIDING
SOMETHING.
>> THAT'S A RELATABLE ONE.
>> YOU, SIR NEED TO STEP UP
BECAUSE SHE'S LETTING YOU KNOW
SOMETHING SIMPLE THAT COULD
MAKE YOU VERY HAPPY.
WHY WOULDN'T YOU IF IT WOULD
MAKE HER FEEL GOOD.
IF SHE'S SOMEONE YOU LOVE, WHY
WOULDN'T YOU DO THAT.
>> WHAT'S WRONG WITH OUR
DYSFUNCTION HALL FAMILY?
>> I'M MOSTLY WORRIED ABOUT YOU
AND SAM, JEFF.
>> WE HEARD A LITTLE BIT ABOVE
NORMAL IN CERTAIN AREAS.
I GET THAT A LOT.
FIVE MINUTES AGO.
>> COMING UP ON "DBL," A LOT OF
PEOPLE ARE SAYING ESQUIRE
MAGAZINE MISSED THE MARK WITH
THIS COVER AND ANSON WILLIAMS
FROM "HAPPY DAYS" SETTLES THE
SCORE.
WHO'S COOLER POTSY OR THE FONZ?
>>> TODAY'S WATCH AND WIN WORD
IS SUNGLASSES.
>> WELCOME BACK TO "DBL."
ALL MONTH LONG I'M TALKING WITH
TV LEGENDS FROM THE PAST TO
FIND OUT WHERE THEY ARE NOW.
SO I HEADED TO THE HOLLYWOOD
MUSEUM IN THE HEART OF LOS
ANGELES, CALIFORNIA AND SAT
DOWN WITH ANSON WILLIAMS,
BETTER KNOWN AS POTSIE FROM
MONDAY, TUESDAY, HAPPY DAYS.
CHECK THIS OUT.
MONDAY, TUESDAY, I'M IN HEAVEN.
IT WAS A VERY GOOD OPENING.
I'M HERE WITH SOMEONE I'VE
ALWAYS HAD A CRUSH ON.
IT'S ANSON WILLIAMS.
>> THOSE ARE ORIGINAL LYRICS.
I'VE NEVER HEARD THOSE BEFORE.
>> YOU PLAYED ONE OF THE MOST
ICONIC CHARACTERS ON TV.
DO YOU HAVE A FAVORITE MEMORY?
>> THE BEST MEMORY, WE A
SOFTBALL TEAM AND WE WENT ALL
AROUND THE WORLD.
>> WHAT WAS YOUR TEAM NAME?
>> LET ME GUESS, HAPPY DAYS.
>> SO YOU WERE BEST FRIENDS
WITH RICKY CUNNINGHAM, RON
HOWARD, WHICH ONE MADE YOU
LAUGH MORE.
>> LOOK AT THE CHARACTER
FONZIE.
>> DO YOU STILL KEEP IN TOUCH?
>> WE DO.
WE'VE BEEN FRIENDS FOREVER.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE HAD CRASH ON
YOU BUT EVER WANTED TO BE
FONZIE?
>>  WHO WOULDN'T WANT TO BE
FONZIE.
I LIKE POTSIE BETTER.
>> I HEARD ONE OF THE BEATLES
CAME BY.
>> YOU'RE ON A SET, HAPPY.
THERE'S A GUY STANDING BY THE
COFFEE MACHINE LOOKS LIKE JOHN
LENNON.
OH, YEAH, JOHN LENNON CAME HERE
TO HANG OUT WITH US.
YOU BET.
IT WAS JOHN LENNON COMING TO
HANG OUT WITH US.
WE'RE PROFESSIONALS.
WE DON'T ASK FOR ANYBODY.
, ON THIS SHOW IT WOULD BE THE
FIRST.
A VERY NICE LOOKING MAN.
EXCUSE ME, I DON'T MEAN TO
INTERRUPT.
IT'S JULIAN LENNON.
40 YEARS LATER.
CAN WE TAKE A SELFIE.
>> THAT'S A GREAT STORY.
YOU FOUND A WAY TO CURE RATE IT
IN ONE AREA.
IT'S THE BEST.
>> THANK YOU, ANSON WILLIAMSS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SUBSCRIBE TO OUR YOUTUBE
CHANNEL TO CHECK OUT AN
EXTENDED INTERVIEW.
IT'S A SIMPLE SOLUTION TO
COMBAT DROWSY DRIVING AND IT
CLAN SAVE LIVES.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "DBL."
WHETHER YOU'RE MORE OF A DATE
NIGHT OR THE GIFT GIVING TYPE
ON VALENTINE'S DAY, MY GIRL
TORY HAVE SOME TIPS.
YOU KNOW WHO IT IS.
IT'S PRESENTED BY CAR SHIELD.
TORY, WHAT'S A PERFECT VALENTINE
VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> AT THE END OF THE DAY I'M
WRITING A COUPON FOR A HUG.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> I THINK VALENTINE'S DAY IS
EMBARRASSING.
I GOT A PIZZA BUT I CUT IT IN
THE SHAPE OF A HEART.
>> WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
>> I DON'T LIKE ROSE PETALS
LEADING TO THE BEDROOM WITH THE
CEILING FAN.
IT'S THE SAME BEDROOM.
YOU JUST STRAIGHTENED OUT THE
COMFORTABLE.
>> TO AVOID LAST-MINUTE HASSLE
WE HAVE SUGGESTIONS.
DISCUSS EXPECTATIONS WITH YOUR
PARTNER.
ENJOY THE GIFT WITH CAR SHIELD.
THEY PROTECT ITS MEMBERS CALL 1-
800-505-9619 FOR A FREE QUOTE.
>> WELL, YOU AND AL ALWAYS HAVE
SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT IN
THOSE CARS.
>> I LIKE THAT YOU AGREE THAT
ROMANCE IS EMBARRASSING.
>> I THINK IT'S SEXY.
>> HE'S SAYING TO WATCH IT.
>> WEIRD TO SEE.
>> WILL HAVE A PHONE CALL WITH
SUSANNE.
IF YOU'RE LEAVING US YOU CAN
WATCH US ON FACEBOOK.
>> A COVER STORY EXPLODES WHEN
ESQUIRE HIGH LIGHTS A CAUCASIAN
TEEN DURING BLACK HISTORY
MONTH.
DID THEY MISS THE MARK OR IS IT
MUCH TO DO ABOUT NOTHING.
PLUS, FOOD FIGHT.
WHY COUNTRY STAR MIRANDA
LAMBERT DUMPED A PERFECTLY GOOD
SALAD INTO A LADY'S LAP.
DID SOMEONE CALL THE DOCTOR?
THIS PRESIDENTS DAY,
HAVERTYS IS HONORING
PRESIDENT MOM.
SHE MADE THE EXECUTIVE DECISION
TO BUY STORE BOUGHT COOKIES
FOR THE BAKE SALE.
SHE PARDONED EMMA FOR...
BEING EMMA.
AND THEN THERE WAS THE WHOLE
CONE CRISIS THING.
PRESIDENT MOM, THIS PRESIDENTS
DAY SALE IS FOR YOU!
EVERYTHING IS ON SALE.
GET BIG SAVINGS ON SOFAS, BEDS,
DINING SETS AND MORE.
NOW THAT'S FISCALLY RESPONSIBLE
LEADERSHIP.
HAVERTYS.
Life Looks Good.