FO
>>> THIS IS "DAILY BLAST LIVE".
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT WHAT YEAR
TALKING ABOUT.
>> BECAUSE EVERYONE IS TALKING
ABOUT THIS.
>> ALWAYS LIVE, ALWAYS REAL,
ALWAYS UNPREDICTABLE.
>> YOU'RE TOTALLY OFF BASE
HERE.
>> LOG ON AND JOIN OUR LIVE
CONVERSATION.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M SAYING
THIS.
I DO AGREE WITH YOU.
>> DBL STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> 3,2,...
>>> WELCOME TO DBL.
IT IS FRIDAY, FEBRUARY 8th,
2019.
YES, WE ARE LIVE AND WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
I'M HERE WITH TORY, JEFF, AL
AND I'M SAM.
LET'S GET STARTED.
THE RICHEST MAN IN THE WORD
SAYS HE IS BEING EXTORTED AND
EXTORTED AND BLACKMAILED.
JEFF SAYS THE COMPANY IS TRYING
TO EXTORT HIM WITH EXPLICIT
PHOTOS.
THIS ALL STEMMED FROM THE
NATIONAL ENQUIRER STORY ABOUT
HIS AFFAIR WHICH INCLUDED
PRIVATE TEXTS BETWEEN THE TWO.
HE HIRED AN INVESTIGATORS TO
FIND OUT HOW THEY GOT THOSE
TEXTS BUT NOW HE CLAIMS A.M.
I THROUGH A LAWYER TRIED  TO
GET HIM TO HOLD OFF ON HIS
INVESTIGATION OR ELSE THEY
WOULD PUBLISH THE PHOTOS WHICH
INCLUDES A QUOTE BELOW THE
BELT.
THERE IS A POTENTIAL POLITICAL
ANGLE TO THE STORY AS HE OWNS
THE WASHINGTON POST WHICH HAS
BEEN VERY CRITICAL OF THE
PRESIDENT.
MEANWHILE AMI HAS A PLEA
AGREEMENT OVER THE HUSH MONEY
PAYMENTS DURING THE 2016
PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN THAT MAY
HAVE BENEFITED DONALD TRUMP.
THEY SAID IT ACTED LAWFULLY AND
WILL INVESTIGATE THE CLAIMS.
TORY, YOU'RE OUR LEGAL EAGLE.
ANYTHING READING THOSE E-MAILS
SAY IT IS BLACKMAIL EXTORTION
ONE OR ONE.
>> THE FIRST THING YOU HAVE
HAVE TO KNOW THEY WILL TRY TO
GET OUT OF IT.
IT IS BLACKMAIL.
YOU SHOULD NEVER WRITE THIS
DOWN IN E-MAIL BECAUSE IT IS
HORRIBLE, BUT HAVING THAT E-
MAIL IS PROOF OF EVERYTHING.
I THINK JEFF BEZOS HAS NOTHING
TO LOSE HERE.
HIS REPUTATION MAY HAVE GONE
DONE, BUT I SEE PEOPLE ARE
APPLAUDING HIM AND SAYING, HIS
FAMOUS QUOTE IS I THINK I'LL
ROLL THE LOG OVER AND SEE WHAT
CRAWLS OUT.
>> THIS IS WORRY SOME BECAUSE
NOT EVERYONE HAS THE RESOURCES
THAT HE HAS AND IF YOU DO, WHAT
IF MY CHILDREN SEE THIS?
WHAT IF MY BOARD OF DIRECTORS
ARS UPSET BAY THIS.
YOU SEE A COMPANY THAT IS ABOVE
THE LAW.
WITH THAT TYPE OF POWER WHAT
HAVE THEY DONE BEFORE THAT WE
DON'T KNOW ABOUT?
>> WE HAVE THE CATCH AND KILL
STORY THAT WE TALKED ABOUT IN
PREVIOUS SHOWS.
AT THIS POINT, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHY EXTORTION AND
BLACKMAIL ARE NOT TREATED LIKE
THE CRIMES THEY ARE.
THIS IS ILLEGAL.
A LOT OF PEOPLE DON'T HAVE THE
RESOURCES THAT ARE BLACKMAILED
FOR YEARS.
MARIAH CAREY.
SHE IS A PERSON OVEN NOR MUS
MEANS.
WE KEEP SLAPPING PEOPLE ON THE
WRISTS AND YOU GET SIX MONTHS
OF PROBATION.
UNTIL THEY ARE TREATED LIKE
THEY ARE TRUE CRIMES THEY ARE
OR CORRUPTION, I DON'T THINK
WE'LL SEE A CHANGE IN THIS
BEHAVIOR.
>>> ANOTHER SMEAR CAMPAIGN THE
ENQUIRER DID.
CHECK THIS OUT.
>>
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THEY PUT THAT SHE HATES MY
GRAY HAIR.
SHE NEVER REPORTED THAT.
>> THAT IS YOUR SIGNATURE.
LOOK.
>> WHAT IS UP WITH THAT?
>> I KNOW.
>> NOW I'M REALLY DONE WITH THE
INQUIRER.
>> HOW DID THEY GET YOU?
DID TAY LIFT YOUR LEG, GRAB IT
UNDER THE KNEE?
>> FOR THE AMAZING RACE YOU
HAVE TO DO WEIRD POSES, SO...
>> ARE YOU A GOOD GO TO?
>> WHAT DID YOU THINKER, I'M A
DIRECTOR?
>> ARE YOU JEALOUS I'M IN THE
ENQUIRER?
>> TORY.
>> FOR SURE.
>>
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THE PRESIDENT'S DAUGHTER IS
SLAMMING AN ART EXHIBIT RIGHT
NOW AS SEXIST.
THIS IS THE ART EXHIBIT IN D.C.
IT INVITES PEOPLE TO THROW
CRUMBS AT A LOOKALIKE MODEL OF
IVANKA AND THEN VACUUMS THE
YUMS UP.
SHE WAS ASKED ON G.M.
A. HERE IS HER RESPONSE.
>> I THINK IT IS A VERY SEXIST
REPRESENTATION OF A WOMAN BUT
WHAT BOTHERED ME ABOUT THIS
IMAGE IS THAT THEY HIRED A 16-
YEAR-OLD GIRL TO STAND THERE
AND HAVE CRUMBS THROWN AT HER
FOR TWO HOURS A DAY FOR A
COUPLE OF MONTHS.
>> SO I HAVE A REAL PROBLEM
WITH THAT.
>> AND TORY, NOT ONLY ARE YOU
OUR LEGAL EAGLE BUT YOU'RE AN
ART HISTORY MAJOR.
SHOULD IVANKA HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH THIS?
>> NO.
I THINK SHE IS TAKING IT WRONG
AS THE VACUUM IS SEX EXIST.
THEY ARE NOT THROWING CRUMBS AT
HER OR THE LOOKALIKE.
THE WHOLE IDEA WHO IS THE
ARTIST IS IT IS MAKING FUN OF
US, THE VIEWERS WHO ARE
THROWING THE BREADCRUMBS SO SHE
HAS TO CLEAN UP THE MESS AND IT
SHOWS HOW MUCH WE ENJOY THE
MESS, AND TO WATCH IT BE
CLEANED UP.
HER CLEANING UP HER FATHER OR
THE ADMINISTRATION.
>> YES AND WE KEEP THROWING
STUFF AT HER TO SEE WHAT SHE
WILL CLEAN UP.
IT IS A VERY BIG
INTERPRETATION.
I THINK SHE USED TOO MUCH OF A
LITERAL INTERPRETATION.
IT IS PROF VACATION.
>> BUT SOME PEOPLE WITH ART,
YOU HAVE EVERY RIGHT TO THE
INTERPRETATION.
YOU HAD A DIFFERENT
>> YES.
I'M SURPRISED BY YOUR REACTION
IN THIS ME TOO MOVE: THIS IS
KIND OF SEXIST.
I DON'T THINK A WOMAN WITH A
VACUUM IS IN ANY WAY
ENLIGHTENING.
I GET THE ART FORM BUT I DON'T
THINK IT IS COOL.
>> WHAT ARE WORDS YOU THINK OF?
>> '60s.
ANTIQUE QUITED.
>> EXACTLY.
>> SO THAT IS THE POINT.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SEE HER AS
THIS ROLE MODEL, 1950s "LEAVE
IT TO BEAVER" ON THE OUTSIDE,
BUT ON THE INSIDE SHE IS
CLEANING UP EVERY BODY'S MESS
AND THERE IS THAT "LEAVE IT TO
BEAVER."
>> BUT BECAUSE IT IS TRUMP,
THEY INTERPRET IT AS ART BUT IF
IT WAS THE OBAMAS IT WOULDN'T
BE INTERPRETED THAT WAY.
>> IF IT WAS MICHELLE OR
SOMETHING I DON'T THINK THEY
WOULD HAVE BEEN ANGRY BUT
HOPEFULLY INTERPRETED IT AS AN
ART PIECE.
>> WE INTERPRET IT DIFFERENT.
>> WE HAVE SAD NEWS TO SHARE.
ACTOR ALBERT FINNEY PASSED AWAY
AT 82.
HE RECEIVED FIVE OSCAR
NOMINATIONS FOR HIS ROLES IN
TOM JONES, MURDER ON THE ORIENT
EXPRESS AND ERIN BROCKOVICH AND
HE WAS IN ANNIE.
I LOVED HIM IN BIG FISH.
HIS FAMILY SAID HE PASSED AWAY
PEACEFULLY AFTER A SHORT
ILLNESS WITH THOSE CLOSEST TO
HIM BAY HIS SIDE.
WE'RE ALSO REMEMBERING FRANK
ROBINSON, HE WAS THE FIRST
AFRICAN-AMERICAN MANAGER IN
MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL.
HE PASSED AWAY.
HE WON MVP IN BOTH LEAGUES.
>> I ALWAYS LOOK AT YOU,
BECAUSE YOU FOCUS ON THEIR
LEGACY.
>> WE NOT THAT IS WAITING FOR
ALL OF US.
THE ONLY THING WE CAN CONTROL
IS WHAT WE'RE DOING RIGHT NOW.
HOW YOU HANDLE TODAY.
YOU LOOK AT THE LIVES THAT
FRANK ROBINSON HAD AND, I MEAN,
WHAT ELSE DO YOU WANT?
BUT PASS AWAY AT HOME WITH YOUR
GRANDKIDS AROUND THE BED.
THAT IS COOL.
THAT IS THE GOAL.
IT IS NOT COOL WHEN YOU'RE 20
AND YOU'RE OUT AT THE NIGHTCLUB
AND SOMETHING HAPPENS.
WHEN YOU ARE AT HOME AND GET TO
DIE WITH THE PEOPLE WHO LOVE
YOU, I'M ALL FOR THAT.
>> AMEN.
>> WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>> THIS FEBRUARY, "DAILY BLAST
LIVE" AND SANDALS RESORTS WANT
YOU TO FALL IN LOVE ALL OVER
AGAIN.
WE'RE GIVING AWAY A TRIP FOR
YOU AND YOUR SPECIAL SOMEONE TO
ONE OF SANDALS LUXURY INCLUDED
VACATION HOT SPOTS.
JUST WATCH DBL FOR THE WORD OF
THE DAY AND GO TO "DAILY BLAST
LIVE.COM"/SANDALS TO ENTER.
THE MORE WORDS, THE MORE
CHANCES TO WIN.
THE WINNER WILL BE ANNOUNCED
LIVE ON DBL FEBRUARY 27th.
HOW COULD YOU NOT LOVE THAT?
>>> "BEST FIENDS."
COLLECT JO JO AND TONS OF OTHER
CUTE CHARACTERS.
SOLVE THOUSANDS OF FUN PUZZLES
KS DOWNLOAD "BEST FIENDS" TODAY
FOR FREE.
BEST FRIENDS WITHOUT THE "R."
"BEST FIENDS."
>>> SNACKING HAS NEVER BEEN
THIS EXCITING.
TO GET YOUR OWN FREE SAMPLER
BOX GO TO GRAZE.COM AND ENTER
EAT 56 AND
>>> WELCOME BACK TO DBL.
THEY ARE CRACKING DOWN OF THE
POSTING AND SHARES CHECKPOINTS
>>> THEY SENT A CEASE AND
DESIST LETTER TO GOOGLE TO STOP
SHARING THIS.
THE DEPARTMENT SAYS POSTING THE
LOCATIONS OF DWI CHECKPOINTS IS
LIKELY GROUNDS FOR ENGAGING IN
CRIMINAL CONDUCT BECAUSE IT
COULD BE USED TO AID IMPAIRED
AND INTOXICATED DRIVERS AND
BYPASSING CHECKPOINTS AND
ENCOURAGES THAT DRIVING.
>>> CHASTITY FROM FACEBOOK SAYS
THE APP DOESN'T NECESSARILY
SHOW COLLECT POINTS.
IT IS ALLOWS PEOPLE TO TIP-OFF
OTHER DRIVERS WHERE THE POLICE
ARE LOCATED.
THEY ARE MAKING IT SOUND LIKE
THEY ARE EXPOSING CHECKPOINTS.
IT TRULY HELPS ME SLOW DOWN
WHEN I'M DRIVING.
>> LOOK AT YOU WITH THE
CONSPIRACY THEORY.
THAT SOUNDS RIGHT FOR DUIs ARE
A BIG SOURCE OF REVENUE FOR
POLICE AN WELL AS SPEEDING
TICKETS.
WHEN THEY SAY A COP IS 100 FEET
AHEAD, THEY DON'T LIKE THAT.
>> YOU WANT TO GO HIGHER WITH
YOUR VOICE?
>> I WAS HURT.
>>
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> SHOCKED.
>> I AM SO SORRY.
KAREN SAID IT HAS TO DO WITH
THE GOTCHA MENTALITY OF THE
COPS.
>> SOMETHING VERY INTERESTING
FOR ME IS YOU AREN'T ALLOWED TO
STOP A CAR UNLESS YOU HAVE
PROBABLE CAUSE BECAUSE YOU HAVE
RIGHTS TO PRIVACY WHICH I'M BIG
ON.
SO IF YOU HAVE A D.U.I.
CHECKPOINT WHERE THEY CHECK
EVERY CAR, THEY HAVE TO
ANNOUNCE IT SO EVERY STATE YOU
HAVE TO HEAR FROM THE POLICE IF
YOU HAVE A SCANNER.
ALL THEY ARE DOING IS PUTTING
IT IN THERE.
I WANT MY PRIVACY KEPT CLEAN.
>> BUT WHAT ABOUT IF YOUR
PRIVACY IS INFRINGING ON THE
SAFETY OF MY LOVED ONES?
I HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THAT.
WHEN IT COMES TO DRINKING AND
DRIVING I HAVE ZERO TOLERANCE
AND FOR DECADES WE HAVE HAD
THESE CHECKPOINTS AND THEY HAVE
LEGITIMATELY TAKEN PEOPLE OFF
THE ROAD THAT COULD HAVE KILLED
ONE OF MY LOVED ONES, SO I
AGREE.
I DON'T THINK WA ZE SHOULD BE A
RED FLAG WHERE THE CHECKPOINTS
ARE.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH THEY
ARE LOOKING OUT FOR OUR SAFETY.
I THINK IT IS A MINI PLAY.
>> BUT THE END RESULT IS TAKING
THEM OFF THE ROAD.
>> IF YOU'RE DRIVING DRUNK,
YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
UBERS ARE $5.
>> BUT SOME PEOPLE LIVE
PAYCHECK TO PAYCHECK.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DRINKING FOR
THEN.
>> JUST TAKE AN UBER.
>>> COMING UP, WE HAVE THE MUST
HAVE GIFTS THAT WILL WOW YOUR
SWEETHEART THIS V DAY.
NEXT WE'RE CHATTING WITH THE
STARS OF THE LATEST PROJECT.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK WITH
THAT.
>>> HI.
I'M MATT McCOY.
FOR PEOPLE AS EXPERIENCED AS
YOU AND ME, CAREFUL DRIVING
COMES NATURALLY.
ALL THAT EXPERIENCE SHOULD BE
WORTH SOMETHING AND IT IS.
WITH THE AARP AUTO INSURANCE
PROGRAM FROM THE HARTFORD.
SWITCHING SAVED ME HUNDREDS.
FOUR OF FIVE MEMBERS 50 AND
OVER WHO SWITCHED FROM
COMPANIES LIKE ALLSTATE, STATE
FARM AND GEICO, GOT A LOWER
RATE WITH THE HARTFORD.
>> I GOT BETTER POLICY AND
COVERAGE AND A BETTER RATE AS
WELL.
>> DRIVERS 50 AND OVER LIKE TO
SAVE MONEY, BUT IT IS GREAT
WHEN IT COMES WITH COVERAGE AND
BENEFITS DESIGNED FOR US.
THAT IS REAL VALUE.
CALL FOR YOUR FREE QUOTE.
NOT AN AARP MEMBER, THE
HARTFORD HELPS YOU JOIN IN
MINUTES.
THEY RESPECT THE CUSTOMERS
ENOUGH TO DO THE RIGHT THING,
LIKE WITH NEW KARRIE  KNEW CAR
SPACE REPLACEMENT.
THEY WILL PAY THE FULL COST.
SOMETIMES LIFE HAPPENS AND WHEN
IT DOES, IT IS IMPORTANT TO
KNOW THE BUSINESS YOU'RE DOING
BUSINESS WITH HAS YOUR BACK.
THEY HAVE MY BACK.
>> THEY OFFER LIFETIME RENEW
BUILT.
THAT IS THE HARTFORD'S PROMISE
NOT TO DROP YOU EVEN IF YOU
HAVE HAD AN ACCIDENT.
>> IT IS A GREAT FEELING AND
COMFORTABLE FEELING TO KNOW I'M
NOT GOING TO GET DROPPED FOR
THAT REASON.
>> I FEEL LIKE I HAVE A PARTNER
IN THE HARTFORD AND I CAN TRUST
THEM WHEN AND IF I NEED THEM.
>> YOU CAN SAVE HUNDREDS OF
DOLLARS IF YOU SWITCH AND GET
NEW KARRIE PLACEMENT AND
LIFETIME RENEW BUILT.
>> I WOULD RECOMMEND THE
HARTFORD TO FRIENDS, RELATIVES,
ANYBODY.
>> CERTAINLY WHEN WE NEEDED
THEM, THEY WERE THERE FOR US.
ITS IMPRESSIVE.
>> CALL 1(800)683-7118 TO
REQUEST YOUR FREE QUOTE.
THAT IS 1(800)683-7118 OR GO TO
GO HARTFORD AUTO.COM.
>> THE WATCH AND WIN WORD IS
INCLUSIVE.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO DBL.
CRITICS ARE CALLING JAMES
CAMERON'S NEWEST MOVIE
MESMERIZING AND ASTONISHING.
IT IS THE LATEST ATTEMPT AT
PUSHING HIGH-TECH BOUNDARIES
AFTER HIS 2009 SHOW AVATAR.
>>> THIS BODY, I FEEL A
CONNECTION TO IT.
I CAN'T EXPLAIN.
>> HELLO, EVERYONE.
>> HELLO.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> I SAW YOU IN ACTION AND I
CAN ONLY IMAGINE HOW HARD IT
MUST HAVE BEEN TO KISS SOMEONE
THROUGH A KIND OF MOTION SUIT.
HOW IS THAT?
>> SEXY.
>> WAS THERE ANY TONGUE ACTION
OR LIKE A CLAW IN A MASK?
>> NO, NO.
MY FACE IS RIGHT THERE.
FOR BETTER OR WORSE, THAT IS ME
UP THERE.
>> WHAT IS IT LIKE DIRECTING
SOMEONE WHO IS THERE THAT YOU
CAN'T SEE THE FINAL THING IN
THAT MOMENT?
>> TOUCH HIM AGAIN AND I WILL
KILL YOU.
>> IT WAS KIND OF DAUNTING.
I WAS WONDERING WHAT IS MY
ACTRESS GOING TO EVEN LOOK LIKE
BECAUSE I'M SO USED TO ROSA
BEING THERE.
IT WAS LIKE WHAT IF I DON'T
LIKE HER AS MUCH AND WHEN IT
WAS DONE, IT WAS LIKE OH IT IS
ROSA.
IT IS STILL ROSA EVEN THOUGH
THE PROPORTIONS ARE DIFFERENT,
IT IS A DIFFERENT FACE.
>> LAST NIGHT I SAW YOU KISS
SOMEONE THAT WASN'T ACTUALLY
THERE.
>> THAT IS LIKE THE ULTIMATE
CATFISH.
>> HELLO FELLOW LONDONER.
>> HELLO DARLING.
>> WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE TO DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT MAYBE WHEN
TECHNOLOGY GETS THAT FAR I'LL
BE LIKE ACTUALLY I WANT MY
WHOLE BLOOMING BODY.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
CHATTING.
>> WHAT WAS IT'S LIKE PLAYING
SUCH A DIFFERENT CHARACTER AND
WHAT DO YOU PREFER THE MEAN GUY
OR THE LOVING FATHER FIGURE?
>> WHY WOULD THAT BE A
CONTRADICTION?
MEAN GUYS CAN BE LOVING FATHERS
AND LOVING FATHERS CAN BE MEAN.
EVERYBODY HAS EVERYTHING.
IT IS JUST THE PROPORTION THAT
TO WHICH IT IS DISTRIBUTED IN
1%NAL TY IS WHAT I'M CALLED
UPON TO DISCOVER AS AN ACTOR.
>> CAN I ASK YOU A BOUGHT BEING
A DOCTOR IN THE NAVY?
WHAT SIDE WOULD YOU WANT TO
BETTER YOURSELF?
>> THAT WOULD DEPEND WHAT I
NEED.
I'M WELL SERVED WITH WHAT I
HAVE GOT.
I LIKE BEING A HUMAN TRYING TO
MAKE WHAT I HAVE WORK PROPERLY.
>> BUT THIS TIME YOU'RE SO
LOVING AND SO SWEET AND  --
THAT IS WHO I REALLY AM.
>> ARE YOU TELLING ME THE
TRUTH?
>> NO.
>> WHAT YOU THINK YOU KNOW
ABOUT ME FROM WATCHING OTHER
MOVIES, COME ON.
REALLY?
>>
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> GREAT INTERVIEW.
OUR DIGITAL TEAM POSTED A
REVIEW OF THE MOVIE.
CHECK IT OUT ON OUR YouTUBE
PAGE.
COMING UP, SHE DROPS IT IN THE
BIG BROTHER HOUSE.
FIND OUT HOW SHE IS HELPING
OTHERS DROP THE POUNDS AND KEEP
THEM OFF.
NEXT IN OUR DBL HEALTH BLAST.
>>> PROMOTIONAL CONSIDERATION
IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY...
WOULDN'T YOU LIKE TO WAKE UP
EVERY MORNING WITH HAIR THAT
LOOKS HEALTHY, FULL AND
BEAUTIFUL?
WELL NOW, YOU CAN WITH
CLINICALLY PROVEN VIVISCAL, THE
NUMBER ONE DRUG FEEL SUPPLEMENT
MADE FOR EVERY WOMAN OF EVERY
HAIR TYPE.
IN AS LITTLE AS THREE MONTHS IT
CAN INCREASE VOLUME BY 30% AND
SHEDDING BY 40% GUARANTEED.
RIGHT NOW A THREE MONTH SUPPLY
OF THE VIVISCAL ADVANCED HAIR
HEALTH SUPPLEMENTS CAN BE YOURS
FOR THE LOW PRICE OF ONLY
$39.99 FOR THE FIRST MONTH'S
SUPPLY AND FOR THE FIRST TIME
EVER WE'LL INCLUDE A FREE
VIVISCAL GORGEOUS EL KICK XOR.
GET ALL THESE GIFTS VALUED AT
OVER $100 FREE.
AND SHIPPING IS FREE.
CALL 1(800)950-3117 OR GO
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
%
>>> WELCOME BACK TO DBL.
TEN YEARS AGO ROBIN NICHOLS
MADE SIMPLE CHANGES TO HER LIFE
THAT LED TO AN INCREDIBLE
TRANSFORMATION.
SHE LOST MORE THAN 100 POUNDS
AND KEPT IT OFF.
BRANDON LONDON CAUGHT UP WITH
HER.
>>> HI ROBIN.
I'M BRANDON LONDON.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> THANK YOU FOR SHARING YOUR
STORY WITH DBL NATION.
YOU LOST 100 POUNDS TEN YEARS
AGO.
WHAT ARE SOME OF THE THINGS
THAT CAUSED YOU TO BECOME OVER
WEIGHT?
>> FROM AS EARLY AS I CAN
REMEMBER LOOKING AT PICTURES OF
MYSELF AS A BABY, I'M
OVERWEIGHT AND THERE IS FOOD IN
MY MOUTH AND THERE IS CHOCOLATE
OR ICE-CREAM AND I'M ASLEEP AND
COVERED IN STUFF.
>> WHEN DID YOU HIT ROCK
BUTTON?
>> AFTER THE BIRTH OF OUR
SECOND CHILD I WENT SHOPPING
AND I COULDN'T FIT IN THE
LARGER SIZE AND I REMEMBER
BEING LIKE OH, MY GOD.
I REMEMBER FORCING MYSELF TO
TAKE OFF ALL MY CLOTHES AND
LOOK AT MYSELF IN THE MIRROR
AND GRAB AT MYSELF AND BE LIKE
WHAT HAS BECOME OF YOU?
>> WHO ARE SOME OF THE PEOPLE
THAT HELPED YOU OUT AND
MOTIVATED YOU ALONG THE WAY?
>> MY DAD.
MY DAD WAS DEFINITELY HUGE.
MY SISTERS AND MY FAMILY HAVE
ALWAYS BEEN AMAZING.
I STARTED ROBIN'S NEST AS MUCH
TO KEEP MYSELF HEALTHY AND TO
HELP OTHERS SO I OFFER RETREATS
FOR PEOPLE WHO WILL COME STAY
WITH ME AND FOR 72 HOURS I COOK
FOR THEM AND DON'T ALLOW THEM
TO CHEAT AND GET THEM THROUGH
THE DETOX PROCESS.
>> HOW WERE YOU SO CONSISTENT
WHEN IT CAME TO THE 12-STEP
PROGRAM AND IT WASN'T A START
AND STOP THING?
>> I HIT ROCK BOTTOM.
MY DAD WAS DYING.
I HAD TO WATCH HIM DIE.
I WOULD ALWAYS USE FOOD TO
MITIGATE LIFE AND THERE IS
NOTHING ON EARTH THAT COULD
HAVE BEEN HARDER AND THAT IS
WHEN I WALKED INTO THE DOORS OF
THE 12 STEP PROGRAM AND WAS
LIKE PLEASE HELP ME.
>> HOW HAS YOUR LIFE CHANGED
OVER THE LAST TEN YEARS?
IN EVERY WAY.
I'M SKIING, TRYING THINGS I
NEVER WOULD HAVE.
I HAVE SO MUCH GRATITUDE TOR
LIFE.
>> YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO SHOW
US TODAY.
>> I DO.
I DO.
HERE IT IS.
YOU WANT ME TO PUT IT ON?
>> JUST PUT IT OUT REAL QUICK.
I WANT TO SEE THE
TRANSFORMATION FOR SURE.
WOW!
>> IT IS A PRETTY COLOR.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WOW!
WHAT CURRENT ROBIN RIGHT NOW
SAY TO THE ROBIN WHO WAS
WEARING THIS SWEATER?
>> IT REPRESENTS SO MUCH MORE
THAN JUST WEIGHT.
HIDING FROM LIFE AND IT IS
AMAZING TO TAKE IT OFF.
>> WELL, GO AHEAD AND TAKE OFF
THAT CHAIN.
HERE IS THE REBIRTH AND HERE
YOU ARE NOW.
I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
I'M THANKFUL FOR HEARING YOUR
STORY.
>> TO LIVE YOUR LIFE TO THE
FULLEST CALL 1(800)393-6540.
>> WHAT AN INCREDIBLE STORY.
I THINK THAT WILL INSPIRE A LOT
OF PEOPLE AND SEEING EVERYTHING
THAT SHE HAS OVERCOME IN THE
PAST ESPECIALLY WITH HER FATHER
AND IT IS NICE TO SEE SHE IS
TAKING AHOLD OF HER LIFE AND
ENDING UP ON TON.
>> GOOD FOR HER.
>> AND BRANDON LONDON WORKS SO
HARD FOR US AND HE IS GETTING
GREAT AT THESE PIECES.
>> SHE WAS SO COMFORTABLE
TALKING ABOUT THAT.
THE PASSING OF HER FATHER.
YOU SEE THAT WEIGHT.
WHEN PEOPLE SEE PEOPLE OVER
WEIGHT, THEY SAY SHE IS LAZY,
HE IS LAZY.
THERE IS SO MUCH PAIN UNDER
THAT WEIGHT AND GOOD ON HER AND
GREAT JOB BRANDON LONDON.
>> THAT WAS REALLY NICE.
>> WE NEED TO CONTINUE THAT
CONVERSATION IN THE BREAK.
IF YOU'RE LEAVING US RIGHT NOW,
YOU CAN STILL WATCH US LIVE ON
FACEBOOK AND YouTUBE.
HERE IS WHAT IS COMING UP NEXT.
>>> DINA LOEWENS MYSTERY MAN
>>> THE CELEBRITY BIG BROTHER
HOUSE GUEST SAYS SHE HAS BEEN
DATING HIM FOR FIVE YEARS, BUT
YOU WON'T BELIEVE THE ONE THING
THEY HAVE NEVER DONE.
THEN REALITY TV STAR AND
WEDDING PLANNER DAVID TUTERA.
THE CELEBRITY BRIDES TO BE.
HE IS DYING TO HELP.
VALENTINE'S DAY GIFTS THAT WILL
MELT YOUR HONEY'S HEART.
DON'T MISS
THIS PRESIDENTS DAY,
HAVERTYS IS HONORING
PRESIDENT MOM.
SHE MADE THE EXECUTIVE DECISION
TO BUY STORE BOUGHT COOKIES
FOR THE BAKE SALE.
SHE PARDONED EMMA FOR...
BEING EMMA.
AND THEN THERE WAS THE WHOLE
CONE CRISIS THING.
PRESIDENT MOM, THIS PRESIDENTS
DAY SALE IS FOR YOU!
FOR THE NEXT FOUR DAYS, GET
FREE FINANCING FOR FIVE YEARS.
GET BIG SAVINGS ON SOFAS, BEDS,
DINING SETS AND MORE.
NOW THAT'S FISCALLY RESPONSIBLE
LEADERSHIP.
HAVERTYS.
Life Looks Good.