I'm Craig Melvin.
And I'm Natalie Morales.
And this is "Dateline."
ragedy on
top of a tragedy now.
CRAIG MELVIN (VOICEOVER):
It happened so quickly.
Their parents in
the backyard spa.
Their mom in trouble.
My dad just panicked.
CRAIG MELVIN (VOICEOVER): A
sudden slip, a fatal fall.
KEITH MORRISON: You're
losing your mother.
Right.
KEITH MORRISON: You're watching
her go right in front of you.
CRAIG MELVIN
(VOICEOVER): Someone
else was watching her too--
a curious neighbor.
LINDSAY PATTERSON: It was scary.
The look on his face was
almost undescribable.
CRAIG MELVIN (VOICEOVER):
What had she seen?
Was this drowning
really an accident?
CRAIG MELVIN (VOICEOVER):
A husband and father
are suddenly under suspicion.
And he's crying,
and we're crying.
He said, they think I hurt mom.
CRAIG MELVIN (VOICEOVER): Three
daughters stand by their dad.
And one prosecutor stands firm.
He's holding his wife
of almost three decades
under the water.
And my job is to get
justice for Cristi Hall.
CRAIG MELVIN (VOICEOVER):
Was it murder?
[theme music]
Hello, and welcome
to "Dateline."
A young woman peers
into her neighbor's yard
and sees something for a
few mysterious seconds--
a man, a woman, and a
moment that's unsettling.
What she saw and
what she did would
set in motion a chain
of events that would
divide a family and a jury.
Here's Keith Morrison.
We know the truth and we
know everything that happened.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
How do we know what we know?
It's emotionally unsatisfying
not to have that answer.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): So it
is, even if we've seen something
or if we think. we have.
And that's the question at
the heart of the whole puzzle.
Is this woman right?
LINDSAY PATTERSON:
I know what I saw.
And I know the
conclusion of my story.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Of course she does.
So why does this other
woman think this?
She didn't know for
sure what she saw.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
The question, we say,
on which all the rest will turn.
Why don't we begin here?
Calla Mesa, California,
Riverside County.
Historic missions, sprawling
suburbs creeping out
to the rim of mountains
around the eastern flank
of Los Angeles.
Here is where Chris and Cristi
Hall had come to live out
their golden years, though
they were far from old
when it happened.
Just experienced with
life and each other.
As far back as I
can remember, it's
always been Chris and Cristi.
They were never
thought of as separate.
They're-- they're a unit.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
These are the three daughters,
Courtney, Briana, and Ashtin.
And all of them, of course,
have heard scores of times
the story of how
their parents met.
It was 1978.
Cristi had gone to see a
relative at the Air Force
base in nearby San
Bernardino and, quite
by chance, while she
was there, encountered
a security guard who--
to her, at least--
looked just like Elvis.
It was Blair Christopher Hall--
Chris to his friends.
Apparently, she was a
little flirty at the gate.
[chuckling]
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
In short order,
Chris and Cristi got married.
She was 17.
He, 20.
And as the girls
grew up, they said
they never doubted
for a single moment
the powerful bond of love--
their parents with them
and with each other.
I'd venture to say we
were probably closer with
our parents than most children.
They were the parents that
I hoped to one day be.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Cristi, the vivacious glue
of the family.
Chris, her perfect mirror.
ASHTIN HALL: My
dad's a little more
kick back, relax, and quiet.
But they were a perfect
balance, I think.
Yes.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
For years, Chris Hall
was a police officer
in San Bernardino,
until he was shot
in the line of duty.
And then he went off
to become police chief
in two small towns in Idaho.
Then, in 2005,
anticipating an empty nest
and eventual
retirement, the Halls
bought this place back in
Calla Mesa, which they loved
for its backyard pool and spa.
And life in the
spring of 2007 seemed
to have hit a sweet spot, as
Ashtin and Briana remember
their mother telling them.
BRIANA HALL: We happened to
be laying on the bed with her.
She just started talking.
She was like, I am just--
I'm so happy that I
have you girls and dad.
It was kind of one of those
conversations that you--
BRIANA HALL: It
was kind of rare.
--that you don't
have every day.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): Still,
there was work to be done.
It was not a new house;
could use some remodeling,
particularly the bathroom.
Courtney was still living with
her parents as the work began.
--that they were
going to be doing the--
KEITH MORRISON: Right.
--tilework and stuff.
So we wouldn't have a
shower for that day.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
So, shower out of commission,
they decided to wake up early,
put on their bathing suits,
and rinse off in the outdoor
spa before the contractor
arrived at 6:45 AM.
It was June 7, 2007.
Chris got up first, turned
on the spa to warm it up,
and then called Briana at her
college dorm in San Diego.
Here's your
wake-up call, babe.
Get out and go on that run.
KEITH MORRISON:
Back at the house,
Courtney dozed through
her first wake-up,
while Chris and Cristi made
their way outside to the spa.
Just after 6:30, Chris
looked in on Courtney again,
second call, then
headed back to the spa.
Life's last normal moments.
6:37 AM.
I got up out of bed.
And I was putting
on my robe, and I
just heard this panicked--
just panicked scream from
my dad yelling for me.
You know, I ran down the
hallway to the back porch.
And I saw him--
[sighs]
--just trying to pull up
my mom out of the spa.
FEMALE OPERATOR (ON PHONE):
Fire Department and Emergency.
COURTNEY HALL (ON PHONE):
[inaudible] an ambulance.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): It
was she who dialed 911 as she
and her father struggled to
lift her mother out of the spot.
It was the first moments of
the worst day of our lives.
Is it possible for people
to understand what it's
like to be in that situation?
I don't think so.
It's-- to see just both your
parents in the worst times
that you've ever seen them.
Obviously, my mom unconscious,
and my dad just panicked.
And for the first time in my
life, seeing him just that way,
not knowing what to do.
Because he was a cop,
he was used to dealing
with those kinds of things.
He was a cop.
He's used to dealing with
those kinds of things
with people that
were not his wife.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
So Courtney took charge.
After calling 911, she
started CPR on her mother
with her father.
EMT and firefighter Eric Norwood
was the first to respond.
He just started--
help my wife.
Oh my god, help my wife.
Help my wife.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): Chris Hall
was kneeling at his wife's side,
more in the way than anything,
and so hysterical it was
hard for the EMTs to help.
ERIC NORWOOD (VOICEOVER):
It took us a little bit
to get him out of the way.
He didn't want to leave her.
He was just holding her
hand, yelling her name.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
The paramedics worked on Cristi
for more than 20 minutes.
No vital signs.
None.
And-- and no words
to describe just
the-- the fear and the anxiety.
You're losing your mother.
Right.
And you're watching her
go right in front of you.
We tried to save her
together and we just couldn't.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): The ambulance
rushed her off to the hospital,
where she was declared dead.
She had drowned
in the family spa.
A private family tragedy, except
maybe not so private after all.
Someone was watching.
CRAIG MELVIN (VOICEOVER):
"Dateline" returns
after the break.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): On
the morning of June 7, 2007,
Briana Hall was on the
road from San Diego,
driving home from college.
To what, she didn't know,
except that her elder
sister, Courtney, had
called and it sounded bad.
She said there
was an accident.
You need to just, you
know, come home right away.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): It was
Courtney who eventually broke
the news to Ashtin and Briana.
Their mother, their father's
wife of close to 30 years,
was dead.
But neither Courtney nor
Chris waited at the house
to tell the sisters what
happened or to comfort them,
nor did they linger over
the body at the hospital.
They couldn't, because father
and daughter were escorted
to separate squad cars and
driven to the police station
to talk about the accident.
What was that ride like?
Quiet, you know?
I just remember
crying the whole time.
I couldn't comfort my father.
He couldn't comfort me.
He was-- when we
got to the station--
and they said that my dad would
just be a few more minutes.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): Chris,
so frenzied at the scene,
had calmed down by then.
He was a cop among
cops, after all.
And he understood, he said,
what was necessary to help
them sort out what happened.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Happy to help, he said.
Whatever would get him back
home to comfort his daughters
as quickly as possible.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): Chris told
investigators what happened.
How as Courtney
slept, he and Cristi
were in the spa, bathing.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
As Cristi returned to the spa,
said Chris, they passed
each other on the patio.
He went in the house,
then, he said, stopped
by Courtney's room to
make sure she was awake,
then went right back outside--
and saw his wife floating
face down in the spa.
He called Courtney
then, he said,
and they began a frantic
effort to revive her.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): From what?
A fall?
Must've been.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): But Chris
apparently hadn't noticed
the nasty 3-inch laceration
on Cristi's head.
And here, suddenly, the
point of the police interview
is revealed.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): Not consistent
with just falling down?
Why would the police think that?
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): Why, in fact,
was this ex-police chief
being questioned at all
about the apparently
disastrous accident that
killed the love of his life?
And the answer was
right next door.
When Chris and Cristi Hall took
their outdoor bath that morning
in June, someone was watching--
her.
I got up at 6:00,
got my coffee.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Lindsay Patterson
was on leave from her IT job
in the Navy, visiting her mom,
who lives just over the backyard
wall from the Hall house.
Lindsay was inside, in the
bathroom that faced away
from the Hall house and
out on to the street,
when she heard a noise.
It was a horrible scream.
It was just something-was-wrong
kind of scream.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
A woman's, she thought.
She went outside
to tell her mom.
And I said, did
you hear that scream?
And she said, yeah, but I think
it's just kids playing in the--
playing in the pool.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): Kids?
At 6-something in the morning?
Lindsey walked over to the
6-foot brick wall between
their yard and the Halls'.
She stepped on the planter, she
said, and looked over the wall.
At that point, I saw a
man with, um, his hand--
one hand on top
of a woman's head,
and then one hand on her back.
And she was face
down in the water.
Like something was going on?
Yeah, it-- that's
what I assumed.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): That
is, she thought she was looking
at a sex act in progress.
I don't know why
it didn't seem right,
but something made me
want to look again.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Perhaps 90 seconds, she said,
between her first
and second looks.
And this time, she said, she
only saw the man in the spa.
He's leaning back, just
relaxed in the hot tub.
But I don't see her.
He's got his elbows back,
and he's just kind of looking
around, like nothing.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Where did the woman go?
Lindsay told her mom
something seemed strange.
She again tells me,
Lindsay, stop being nosy.
Don't worry about it.
Um, but it just
didn't seem right.
It wasn't enough time
for her to have gotten
out and gone inside the house.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): So, said
Lindsay, she went
to the wall again,
her third and final look.
At that point, he was
getting out of the Jacuzzi.
Case And he was in
a very big rush.
And she's still
nowhere to be seen.
The look on his face was
almost undescribable.
It was almost as if he had
just gone into another world.
It was scary.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): It was
instinct that told her something
was wrong, said Lindsay.
So she called 911.
[phone ringing]
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
So now, hours and hours later,
the detectives confronted
Chris with Lindsay's story.
Why, they asked, didn't
her story match his?
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): So now that
question we posed as we began--
did Lindsay Patterson
really know what she saw?
CRAIG MELVIN (VOICEOVER):
"Dateline" returns
after the break
With Advil Liqui-Gels,
you'll ask...
What bad shoulder?
What headache?
Advil is relief that's fast
Strength that lasts
You'll ask...
What pain?
With Advil Liqui-Gels
♪♪
♪ 'Cos I know what it means ♪
♪ To walk along the lonely
street of dreams ♪
♪ Here I go again on my--- ♪
You realize your vows are a
Whitesnake song?
I do.
If you ride, you get it.
GEICO Motorcycle.
15 minutes
could save you 15% or more.
Who do you think
takes more pride
in how they craft
their orange juice?
e corporate executivesk
Coke and Pepsi,ide
the farmers ofcraft
orida's Natural?juice?
Only Florida's Natural
is always
made in Florida
by Florida farmers.
Great Taste.
Naturally.
After his wife's drowning
death in a backyard spa,
police asked Chris
Hall to explain
what happened that morning.
What Chris did not know was that
his neighbor had also talked
to police, and she told
a very different story
than the one Chris was telling.
Here again is Keith Morrison.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Chris and Cristi Hall's three
daughters clung together
in grief and shock
all through the dismal
evening hours of that worst
of all days, June
7, 2007, waiting
for their father to return
from the police station.
And they wondered why
was it taking so long.
Then the phone rang, and
they had their answer.
You know, it--
broken-up words.
And he's crying,
and we're crying.
And that-- that
was when he said,
they-- they think I hurt mom.
I mean, he was very upset.
But he didn't sound surprised
when he said, they think I--
He was crying.
He was upset.
Very upset.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
But by the time
police investigators
were questioning Chris,
remember, they had heard
from Lindsay Patterson.
And at the station, Chris's
version of events in the spa
differed in one crucial detail
from what Lindsay described
seeing that first time
she peered over the wall
and into the Halls' backyard.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
But investigators
were getting a good
look at Cristi's body,
and saw wounds that,
to them, suggested
a struggle, and more than
one nasty blow to the head.
So the police had to choose
which version, Chris Hall's
or Lindsay Patterson's, was
more likely the true story
of what happened.
Tom Dove is a
senior investigator
for the Riverside DA.
I think they felt there
was enough to say this
was not an accidental drowning.
It was clearly much more
suspicious than that.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): And
so before the night was over,
Chris Hall was
arrested and charged
with the murder of his wife.
The girls could stop waiting.
He wasn't coming home.
It was obviously a tragedy,
losing our mother that day.
But this is a tragedy
on top of a tragedy now.
Just because knowing our--
our parents, it's just--
--the farthest
thing from the truth.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): And one
that felt infected by some kind
of madness, said the girls.
Cristi was the love of
their father's life,
after all-- the center
of everything for him.
How, they wondered,
could anyone so
happy in his marriage and his
life be accused of harming her?
And she was happy
too, they said--
as happy as she'd ever been.
They knew it, they said, based
on that mother-daughter talk
they had not long
before she died.
ASHTIN HALL: She
just kept reiterating.
It was how happy she was.
Kind of odd.
And me and Brie will
always cherish that.
Of course, didn't think
much of it at that time.
Yeah.
That that being the last
time we actually saw her.
Kind of burned
into your memories.
Yeah.
KEITH MORRISON: Yeah.
But right or wrong, the legal
trigger had been pulled.
Chris Hall spent
almost two months
in jail, until his daughters
received the payout
from Cristi's life
insurance policy
and used the money to meet
his million-dollar bail.
And then he went back to
what was to be his retirement
retreat to prepare, with
the help of his daughters,
for a murder trial.
That's very surprising, to
have a client in a murder case
out on bail.
But he was a special
man, and, uh,
this was a special situation.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): These
are attorneys who
would eventually
defend him, though at first,
they only heard about the case.
Steve Harmon and Paul Grech.
You've said two things there--
special man, special situation.
I think both of us can say
that this is a man that--
that we like and that we know,
and we don't feel he could
have done anything like this.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): So
Chris Hall and his daughters
prepared for a trial
which they hoped
would make clear to
everybody-- the police,
the neighbor, the world--
that Chris would
not, could not, did
not harm the love of his life.
There was never, in
30 years of marriage--
never one moment of violence.
There was no motive for
this man to kill his wife.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Harmon and Grech
had a look at neighbor Lindsay
Patterson's eyewitness account
and suggested it was really
not conclusive at all.
It was tragically incomplete.
She saw three snapshots.
What is missed by
everyone is the wife
getting into the Jacuzzi,
slipping, falling
into the Jacuzzi,
hitting her head,
going unconscious, and drowning.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
See this sharp corner
sticking out into the spa?
Hitting your head on this would
certainly have opened a gash
and knocked Cristi
out, said the attorney.
She didn't see what was really
happening during the times
when she was not looking.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
That scream that made Lindsay
Patterson look over the wall?
Lindsay, they pointed
out, was in a bathroom
that faced the street.
She wasn't in the backyard
when she says she heard it.
Could have been anybody.
And Courtney, who was inside
her own house near the spa,
didn't hear a thing.
And we don't think
that she's lying.
We just think she
misinterpreted what she saw.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
And anyway, Lindsay,
to a certain
degree, concedes she
didn't know what she was seeing
in her glimpses that morning.
LINDSAY PATTERSON:
Something was wrong.
And yet, you hadn't
really seen any of it.
I-- no.
But I knew something was wrong.
I don't know if in my brain,
I was putting things together.
But from between the
scream, the position that he
was holding her, and then not--
just not having enough time for
her-- her to have gone inside.
So it's like you kind of got
three different snapshots--
Right.
--of something
going on in there.
Right.
And had to kind of work out--
Yeah.
--what this was.
You know, I wasn't
thinking at that point,
oh, this man just
murdered his wife.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): But now,
based largely on that
account, Chris Hall
would go on trial for murder.
And it was a trial
for his daughters too.
BRIANA HALL: He loved her.
They were each
other's best friends.
And-- and this is just--
this is not fair to him,
because he truly loved her
more than-- more than anyone.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
And yet, the prosecutor
was going to try to prove that
this family man and former cop
murdered his wife.
Could it be done?
CRAIG MELVIN (VOICEOVER):
"Dateline" returns
after the break.
With uncontrolled
moderate-to-severe eczema,
or atopic dermatitis,
you never know how
your skin will look.
And it can feel like
no matter what you do,
you're always itching.
But even though you see and
feel eczema on your skin,
an overly sensitive
immune system
deep WITHIN your skin
could be the cause.
So help heal your skin
from within.
With DUPIXENT.
DUPIXENT is not a steroid,
and it continuously
treats your eczema
even when you can't see it.
At 16 weeks,
more than 1 in 3 patients saw
clear or almost clear skin,
and patients saw a significant
duction in itch.
Do not use if you are
allergic to DUPIXENT.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur,
including anaphylaxis,
a severe reaction.
Tell your doctor if you have new
or worsening eye problems,
including eye pain or
changes in vision.
If you are taking asthma
medicines,
do not change or stop
your asthma medicine
without talking
to your doctor.
Help heal your
skin from within.
Ask your eczema specialist
about DUPIXENT.
Pain wants to stop you,
like that's gonna happen.
Icy Hot: Icy to dull,
hot to relax.
Rise from Pain. Icy Hot.
Welcome back.
I'm Craig Melvin.
Chris Hall was charged
in the drowning
death of his wife, Cristi.
As prosecutors were preparing
to lay out their case,
Hall's daughters stood by him,
proclaiming his innocence.
Would anything change their
minds about their dad?
Here again is Keith Morrison.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): Burke Strunsky
is a hard-charging man--
ex-member in good standing of
the San Francisco DA's office,
now senior deputy
DA in Riverside.
That takes skill,
persuasive powers.
Strunsky would need
them in the murder
case against the
former police chief
and family man, Chris Hall.
Mr. Hall on the surface
looks like a loving family man.
He looks like a good father.
He was somebody that had
the support of his family.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): So he did.
But Strunsky wasn't
buying the loving
father and family man bit.
No.
When he heard about Chris Hall's
very obvious grief, the wailing
that went on after the
so-called accident,
the phrase that crossed
his mind was, it's an act.
And I think it was a
wonderful performance
by the defendant of acting
like a bereaved husband.
But when you look at his
actions, um, how little he
did to help his wife--
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): Who
tried harder to save Cristi?
Not Chris, said the
prosecutor, but his daughter.
BURKE STRUNSKY: She called 911.
She helped him get the
body out of the spa.
She is the only one that
did chest compressions.
He had no interest in
truly helping his wife.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): A
matter of opinion, of course.
But Prosecutor Strunsky poked
around in Chris Hall's past
as a policeman.
And what did he find?
This man had an uncanny
ability to fabricate stories.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Seven years earlier,
while Hall was chief of
police in Cascade, Idaho,
he was charged
with and convicted
of misuse of public money.
Embezzled $19,000, spent
10 months in jail--
a white collar
crime, hardly murder.
But what struck the
prosecutor is that he
says Hall tried to cover it up.
To plan a fraud, to lie about
it-- not just lie about it,
but lie about it effectively.
I think that was very telling
ababout who we were dealing wit.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Suddenly, the prosecutor's
prospects were looking better.
At the trial, Strunsky
made Lindsay Patterson
his star witness, of course.
It was her story,
after all, that
got the whole thing started.
But almost as important, he
called the Riverside County
medical examiner, who testified
that those lacerations
in Cristi's head could
not, in his opinion,
have been the result of
a single accidental fall.
And the ME argued
the particular type
of bruising on
Cristi's face and body
was a hallmark of homicide.
Sure.
The totality of
injuries were not
consistent with somebody
slipping and falling,
and then a rescue attempt.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
And there was a clump of hair
in the bottom of the
spa, still entwined with
a broken plastic hair clip.
That, said the prosecutor,
could only have
come from a violent struggle.
When you lose
that amount of hair,
it's not reasonably explained
by any kind of fall.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): There were
some minor hiccups in the case.
Lindsay Patterson, for example,
was a little inconsistent
about how long she looked
over the backyard wall
that first time she
saw something going on.
Was it just a few seconds,
or as long as a minute?
But either way,
said the prosecutor,
Lindsay was sure she
saw physical contact.
That was the important thing.
He was given the opportunity
to explain any physical contact
that could in any way
reasonably explain
what Lindsay Patterson missaw.
In other words, were
they washing each other?
Were they involved in a sex act?
Was there anything that she
could have misinterpreted?
And at the end of
the day, you're
not just stuck with
the fact that Lindsay
Patterson made a mistake.
You have to actually
believe that Lindsay
Patterson really hallucinated
about everything she saw.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
And what made Lindsay's story
all the more convincing,
said Prosecutor Strunsky,
was she told it before finding
out what happened to Cristi.
She dialed 911 a full
minute and a half
before anyone from
the Hall house
did, before Lindsay had
any idea how it would end.
Here's what the jury heard
her say in that call.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): And she
was still on the phone with 911
when Chris Hall came outside
and found his wife's
body floating in the spa,
called out for Courtney.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
The investigator, Tom Dove.
I heard it best
described during the trial
as a cosmic coincidence, that
someone could see something
that they perceived to be
more than just some kind
of kinky action in the
Jacuzzi in the morning,
and then that actually
turned out to be true,
that a woman was actually
drowned in that spa.
That is not a coincidence.
That is what she saw.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
The prosecution's theory?
Somehow, sitting in
the spa that morning,
Chris was overcome by
some private fury--
who knows what?
"A hidden violence" is
what Strunsky called it--
and then killed his spouse when
he thought nobody was looking.
Chris Hall ambushed his
wife, grabbed her by the hair,
slammed her head twice
into the concrete edge.
He's holding his wife of almost
three decades under the water,
showing absolutely no
mercy and no remorse,
and an absolute desire to
end her life at that point.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): And
then the piece de resistance.
BURKE STRUNSKY: He then
gets out of the spa,
walks into the house,
where his plan is
to wake his 22-year-old
daughter, who he--
who he can use as
a alibi witness.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
One little quibble--
why?
In fact, as convinced as
he was of Hall's guilt,
Strunsky conceded the
why was a problem.
Didn't legally have to know,
he said, but he just didn't.
There it was.
It's emotionally unsatisfying
not to have that answer,
not to know the entire
narrative of what happened.
But you'd want to know why
this guy, married to this woman
for almost 30 years,
apparently happily,
would suddenly turn on her
and drown her in the pool.
Right.
And I'm not sure we--
we got the answers
to that specific question.
Uh, [inaudible].
Kind of an important
question, isn't it?
It's an important
question, and a question
that we ask in all
spousal homicides.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
So, proof enough?
Or reasonable doubt?
Almost three years after
Cristi Hall's death,
a Riverside jury
would have to decide.
CRAIG MELVIN (VOICEOVER):
"Dateline" returns
after the break.
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50-85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
THE THREE WHAT?
THE THREE P'S?
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 54 AND I WAS
A SMOKER BUT QUIT.
ALEX, WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I'M 65, RETIRED,
AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
ALSO $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80
AND I'M ON A FIXED INCOME.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
THAT'S LESS THAN 35 CENTS A DAY.
YOU CANNOT BE TURNED DOWN
BECAUSE OF YOUR HEALTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
OPTIONS START AT $9.95 A MONTH,
PLUS, YOU GET A 30-DAY
MONEY BACK GUARANTEE.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
There's little rest
for a single dad,
and back pain made it hard to
sleep and get up on time.
en I found Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid,
plus the 12 hour pain
relieving strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a Better AM.
SHOW YOUR GUT SOME LOVE..
ONLY ACTIVIA HAS BILLIONS OF
OUR LIVE AND ACTIVE PROBIOTICS.
A DELICIOUS WAY TO ENJOY
PROBIOTICS EVERY DAY.
WITH 20 YEARS OF
DEVOTION TO GUT HEALTH.
ACTIVIA. LIKE NO OTHER.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Chris Hall's daughters
sat through every miserable
minute of their dad's
trial for murder here
at the courthouse
in Riverside, California.
Their review of the prosecutor's
portrait of their father?
It was a lie, they said.
It's hurtful to us to hear
someone basically say that he
knows our parents
better than we do,
and he knows our
father's a sociopath,
and that we're blind to it,
and he knows that there was
hidden violence in
our parents' marriage,
and we just didn't see it.
You're basically
telling us that we
don't know that our
whole lives were a lie.
And there's--
That is just--
To top that off,
there's no proof of that.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): Chris Hall
had never been violent,
argued the defense;
had no motive, no reason to
suddenly turn on his wife.
It had to be a freak accident.
So, said the defense, Lindsay
Patterson didn't really
know what she saw.
In fact if she'd really
witnessed Chris Hall drowning
his wife, why, then,
didn't she claim
to see Cristi's body in the
spa when she looked again?
Didn't make sense.
But the highlight was the
Hall daughters' testimony--
emotional, quite powerful.
So it put Prosecutor Strunsky
in a strange position--
at odds with the
victim's own family.
Things were so clear.
If we had any inkling he
had done this, believe me,
we would have said so.
BURKE STRUNSKY: And
I think that's--
And we would have seen it.
I-- I think that
that's what they
truly believe in their hearts.
And, you know, it
weighs on me greatly.
But my job is to get
justice for Cristi Hall.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): Now
it was up to a jury to decide.
After six days of
testimony, two days
of deliberation, they couldn't.
It was a deadlock.
The judge declared a mistrial.
Chris Hall walked out of court
with his family free, but not
quite in the clear, and
nothing at all like a victory
for the Hall daughters.
What was it like to
get that hung jury?
What did you think then?
That was--
That was tragic.
That was devastating to us.
You expected a
not guilty verdict?
- Oh, yes.
- Yeah.
Not a doubt.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Deputy DA Burke Strunsky
was disappointed
too, and was also
determined to retry the case.
But first, he set his
investigator on a mission--
to explore the life and
marriage of Chris Hall.
And what do you know?
In Idaho, where Hall had been
a disgraced police chief,
the investigator uncovered
a startling accusation.
Chris was a
great, great conman.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Former Los Angeles
police officer Jerry
Winkle, the county
commissioner up in Idaho.
But once upon a time, he
was Chris Hall's friend--
that is, before a night of
poker and booze, when, he said,
Hall made a
disturbing revelation
that he'd shot
himself in the leg
when he was a cop
in order to get
medical retirement benefits.
Chris had been drinking beer.
And he came right out and told
me that he had shot himself.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
But there was more.
DA investigator Tom Dove
had discovered a secret--
not in Chris's past,
but in Cristi's.
TOM DOVE: There
had been infidelity
in the marriage for
six years prior,
while Chris Hall was
in custody in Idaho.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Cristi's affair was relatively
brief, years earlier.
But she'd been in phone
contact with the man
just days before she died.
Had Chris found out?
Impossible to know.
But when Investigator Dove
talked to Cristi's coworkers
at the clinic where she
was an x-ray technician,
several of them
said they noticed
a sudden change in her
usually vibrant personality.
One coworker offered more.
She told us that she was
contemplating a divorce.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): If
true-- and it was only an if--
it might well persuade a jury.
But also, Prosecutor Strunsky
needed to explain what Lindsay
Patterson saw or didn't see.
Why didn't she see Cristi's
drowned body when she peaked
over the wall a second time?
We were not able to
explain to the jury
why she didn't see
Cristi at that point.
And I think that allowed the
defense to make the argument
that Cristi Hall was inside.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
The prosecution
hired a water expert to do a
recreation of the Hall spa.
Andrea Zaferes has been
assisting law enforcement
nationwide with
drowning investigations
for the past 20 years.
Zaferes got in the
spa while Strunsky
videotaped from the spot
where Lindsay was watching.
From the center of the pool
and towards where Lindsay was
standing, anywhere I was
laying, you could not be
seen from Lindsay's viewpoint.
So once I sank below the
surface and hit that bottom,
you cannot see me at all
from Lindsay's viewpoint.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): And
now the prosecutor was ready.
In May 2011, one year after
the first jury deadlocked,
Burke Strunsky
went back to court
armed with his new evidence
for a brand-new panel
of Hall's peers.
Jurors heard medical experts
testify about the injuries
to Cristi's head
and, once again,
heard Lindsay's 911 call.
Cristi's coworkers testified
for the prosecution.
And Jerry Winkle traveled
from Idaho to tell jurors
what he thought of Chris Hall.
I was ashamed to admit that
he was once a police officer.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): But
if the prosecution had upped
its game in the year between the
two trials, so had the defense.
That's when well-known
attorneys Steve Harmon
and Paul Grech
entered the scene,
and they came out swinging.
That story about Cristi's
affair, for example?
There's a shadow hanging
over all of this stuff--
um, a very human sort of
shadow-- which is that she was
having a little affair, right?
Had a boyfriend.
Yes, if the husband
knew about it.
But the wife never,
ever mentions it
and tells the husband.
No one tells the husband.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Quite right, said the judge.
And because there
was no evidence
that Chris knew about
his wife's affair,
he ruled it out of the trial.
The story about Hall
shooting himself
for retirement benefits?
That was just
absolutely a lie.
That's wrong.
There was never,
never any evidence,
or indication, or
not even a moment's
breath that he shot himself.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): Anyway,
the story was prejudicial,
said the judge,
so he threw that out too.
As for what Lindsay
Patterson says she saw--
Chris Hall holding his
wife's head underwater--
the defense had prepared its
own visual demonstration,
had taken pictures from
her angle at the wall,
to show that it
could look like two
people were touching in the
spa even if they weren't.
This is what she described
seeing in her testimony.
OK.
But on the closeup,
what do you notice?
KEITH MORRISON:
They're not touching
but they're in position
where they could be.
But that's different
than actually touching.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Again, the Hall
daughters were
there every minute,
their father's
enduring champions.
And this time, more family
members came to court.
Two of Cristi's own siblings
testified for Chris.
And said the same thing--
we have not a doubt in
our minds that this was,
uh, not a moment of violence.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): Mm.
This was not a murder.
The-- the victim's own
sister and own brother.
That's an amazing thing to see.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
Perhaps it was.
But listen to this.
The defense had one more very
significant witness, a witness
who oozed credibility--
the sitting medical examiner
from neighboring San Bernardino
County, who stuck his neck
way out to disagree publicly,
in a court of law, with
the medical examiner
from Riverside.
He found this to be
an accidental death, not
a homicide.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): This was
not some ordinary hired gun.
This was a public official who
said straight out that Cristi's
head injuries could and
perhaps should be explained
by an accidental fall.
He didn't rule out
homicide, though?
He didn't rule out homicide.
But he said the
preponderance of the evidence
was towards an
accidental drowning.
What I've-- I've always
been astounded by this--
with this case is that the
Hall family lives so close
to the San Bernardino border,
if Cristi had slipped and fell
four or five blocks
over, the pathologist
in that county would never
have filed criminal charges.
An accident of geography.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
So now a second jury
would have to sort through
these two sets of allegations,
these two opposing realities,
and decide whether Chris
Hall would turn and
embrace home and his loving
daughters or a pair of
handcuffs and a life in prison.
CRAIG MELVIN (VOICEOVER):
"Dateline" returns
after the break.
It's just a cough.
Yeah right.
And the earth is flat.
Ahhh!!
Treat your cough seriously
with Robitussin CF Max.
Nothing lasts longer
and treats more symptoms for
your cough, cold and flu.
Robitussin. Because
it's never just a cough.
Welcome back.
Chris Hall's first trial
ended in a deadlocked jury.
But with new evidence
presented by both sides
during his retrial,
the jury was finally
able to reach a verdict.
Now, with the conclusion to our
story, here's Keith Morrison.
KEITH MORRISON
(VOICEOVER): May 2011.
For the second time, 12 men
and women of Riverside County,
California filed out
of the courtroom--
a second jury to make a life
decision about Chris Hall.
Did he murder his wife?
Which of the medical
examiners should they believe?
Whose account of the
defendant's character?
And, perhaps most
important, what
did Lindsay Patterson see
when she peeked three times
into the Hall's backyard?
Do you ever have those sort of
little dark moments of the soul
where you think, I may have
misinterpreted, misremembered?
That is something I've
thought about every day,
whether I misinterpreted,
whether I think I saw
something that wasn't there.
I didn't see everything.
Yeah?
But I saw what I saw.
And I know the
conclusion of my story.
I know it.
I know it right here.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): Of
course, Chris Hall's daughters
say they know the truth too--
real thing in their hearts.
I think that we were the
three most critical jurors
in that courtroom.
Believe me, if we had heard
anything or had any inkling
that our father could have done
this, as much as it would hurt
and as much as we
love our father,
we would want justice
for our mother.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER): The
jurors deliberated two days,
then broke for the long weekend.
It was Memorial Day.
Hall's daughters felt good.
Things can only go
so wrong for so long
before something
has to actually--
KEITH MORRISON: Go right.
--go right for us.
We just did a lot of talking
about the future and this,
you know, being over,
this being finished.
And honestly, I was
concerned about dad and how
he was finally going
to be able to grieve
for the loss of his wife.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
And then it was
Tuesday, 8:45 in the morning.
The jury gathered.
And minutes later, a
signal they were ready.
Chris Hall and his
daughters rushed to court.
And in the end, it
was very quick--
guilty of first-degree murder.
Their father would not be
coming home, probably ever.
He's being cuffed and
potentially put away for life.
And yeah, it hurts.
And we are angry about that.
You can still hear
those daughters--
I can.
--accusing you of unfairly
convicting their father.
Absolutely.
It weighs on me.
But at the same time, I know
who I'm dealing with when
it comes to Chris Hall.
In fact, he's the one that's
stolen their mother from them.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
It had been a peculiar fact
of this case that the victims'
and defendants' families
had stood solidly together
against the prosecution.
But what no one knew was the
truth was more complicated.
After the verdict, at
Chris Hall's sentencing,
a letter was introduced.
It was from another of
Cristi Hall's brothers, Billy
Carlton, who, until
now, had said not
one public word about the case.
"We would like to ask His Honor
for the maximum sentence,"
wrote Billy.
"The pain that my family has
suffered through this tragedy
is unforgivable."
And I didn't want
to hurt the girls.
I had to say what
was on my mind.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
There was a deep divide
in Cristi's family, said Billy.
Some of her relatives
believed Chris was innocent.
But he and, he says,
others, including
Cristi's uncle Steve
Mundie, silently
urged on the prosecutor.
Half the family
was convinced he
was innocent and half the
family was convinced he wasn't.
And that's hard to do
when you have a big family
and you all have to be
together every once in a while.
And when it involves a
member as loved as Cristi was.
Exactly.
Does that explain
why this kind of group
of people in the
family decided just
to let justice take its course?
We had talked
about it quite a bit.
I think so.
And you've got to know when
to show up sometimes and when
not to show up, just to keep
what's left of the family
as together as you can have it.
Thank you so much for coming.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
When it was over,
Hall convicted and
sentenced to 25 years
to life, some of
Cristi's relatives
met with Prosecutor
Strunsky and thanked him.
They wanted me to thank
you for putting that guy
away, because he's a murderer.
KEITH MORRISON (VOICEOVER):
And the Hall daughters?
Having lost their beloved
mother, fought to save a father
they adored.
COURTNEY HALL: It's a
devastating reality.
It really is, especially
for our family
that-- now, to say that we were
close is an understatement,
you know?
To go from that to being
not able to be there
with each other, it's, uh--
it's the greatest
heartbreak that anyone
can ever experience, I think.
That's all for this
edition of "Dateline."
I'm Craig Melvin.
Thank you for watching.
[theme music]
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY
VISIT NCICAP.ORG]