.
I'm Craig Melvin.
And I'm Natalie Morales.
nd this is "Dateline."
R: I just
dropped off the children
and he wouldn't
let me in the door.
MAN: It was horrible.
We're normal people, and the
person you're dealing with
is a psychopath.
NATALIE MORALES: It's the
story that haunted the country,
the case of Susan Powell.
WOMAN: I was like,
this can't be real.
And he professed to love them.
NATALIE MORALES: Could
it have been prevented?
SOCIAL WORKER: He
exploded the house.
As you listen to it now,
what does it do to you?
It's excruciating.
NATALIE MORALES: The
911 dispatcher shares
his story about that day.
I wish I had recognized
the urgency of the situation.
NATALIE MORALES: Also,
the startling details
of a plot unfolding.
Nobody knew what was going on.
NATALIE MORALES: And
a father's unraveling.
He just saw there
was no way out.
NATALIE MORALES: Intimate
emails from Susan herself.
The young mother's private
fears in her own words.
It's the genuine belief
of a good many people
that you killed her.
NATALIE MORALES: Her husband
speaks a final eerie interview.
I love my sons
more than anything.
I put them first.
I put my family first.
[theme music]
Hello, and welcome
to "Dateline."
The details are heartbreaking.
The disappearance of
a young mom and what
befell her two little boys.
You'll hear from her
loved ones searching
for answers and justice.
You'll also hear from
her husband, Josh Powell,
in his last in-depth interview.
Words that are even
more haunting now.
Here is Keith Morrison
with "A Family's Story."
KEITH MORRISON: It
is so sad to look
at them now, this apparently
perfectly normal family.
Just a young father
and his two young sons
walking a postcard
shore, skipping
rocks across the surface.
But under the surface
of the man's own skin--
Well, what was
beneath the surface?
How in the name of heaven
did this come to this?
911 OPERATOR: Hi, ma'am.
Were you calling about the
fire on the 8200 block, ma'am?
FEMALE CALLER: Yeah.
He exploded the house.
911 OPERATOR: OK.
Do you know if
anyone's in the house?
FEMALE CALLER: Yes.
There was a man
and two children.
I just dropped off
the children and he
wouldn't let me in the door.
KEITH MORRISON: You'll
hear an exclusive interview
with the man who took
that call and who
has been criticized for not
getting help, immediately.
And you find yourself
vilified really.
What was that like?
Well, it's awful.
Part of the problem is
that, like most people
I think, I was aware
of Josh Powell's story,
but I didn't associate
his name with the story.
KEITH MORRISON: We will retrace
Josh Powell's last steps.
Mysterious trips
to a gas station.
A storage locker where
the police said they
found a quilt with blood on it.
And the bank were, in
the surveillance photo,
he has the look
of a man unglued.
And nobody knew
what was going on.
He took more than three
or four substantial steps
to get ready for his death.
KEITH MORRISON: We'll
hear investigators
try to fathom the unfathomable.
What's the motive for
him killing his kids?
Is it that they started
knowing a little too much?
KEITH MORRISON: And
in his last interview,
we'll hear from
Josh Powell himself
who offered, like the
negative of a film,
a bizarre reversal of the truth.
I love my sons
more than anything.
I put them first.
I put my family first.
KEITH MORRISON: On
February 5th, 2012,
while the rest of the
country was settling down
to watch the Super Bowl,
Josh Powell was setting
a trap for his own young sons.
What happened in there was
really only the last chapter
of a very long, sad
story of fathers and sons
and husbands and wives,
sexual delusions,
murder, suicide, and secrets.
Some of those secrets, no doubt,
were burned up in the fire.
But some things we do know, and
they go to the darkest recesses
of the human heart.
Our story begins years ago
when a cheerful young woman
named Susan Cox fell for Josh.
Chuck and Judy Cox
are Susan's parents.
As they spoke to us, they
confessed they were still
in a kind of shock after
the disaster that claimed
their two young grandsons.
And they recalled so
clearly their early fears
about their daughter's beau.
I had a very bad feeling
every time I saw him.
I even asked my daughter,
"Why are you marrying him?"
KEITH MORRISON: Josh's
sister, Jennifer Graves,
told us that as a child,
she was wary of him too.
When Josh was a boy, he
was troubled in some ways,
wasn't he?
There were some issues, yeah.
KEITH MORRISON: Jennifer
says much of the problems
stemmed from her
father, Josh's father.
She is estranged from him today.
Their mother divorced him
years ago and in court papers
alleged he was abusive.
I was about 14 when
I woke up and realized,
my dad is a wacko.
He's just on a different
trajectory, and not a good one.
KEITH MORRISON: She is
talking about Steven Powell.
You're going to learn much
more about him, later.
What was it about
his trajectory that
bothered you or disturbed you?
He just had a really
negative outlook on life.
He was down on just everything.
KEITH MORRISON: An
outlook he seemed
to have passed on to Josh
which, paradoxically,
seemed to attract Susan.
I think she felt
sorry for him.
He didn't have many friends.
And I think she felt
she could make him happy
and that he would change.
KEITH MORRISON: They
married in the Mormon church
and certainly looked happy
in those early photos.
But later, the
couple moved to Utah.
Moved in temporarily with
Jennifer and her husband Kirk.
What was the relationship like
then, as far as you could tell?
It was a little rough.
She would kind of order
him around a little bit
and he wanted to control
her and not let her
go to some activities with me.
KEITH MORRISON: Josh worked,
sometimes, in real estate
and as a web designer.
When Susan went into labor
with their first child,
says Susan's parents, Josh,
working right there at home,
said he was too busy to
drive her to the hospital.
They did.
And when he finally arrived--
He sits in the back of the
room working on his computer.
While she's in labor.
Yeah.
It was a really odd experience.
KEITH MORRISON: They
named the baby Charlie.
Braden followed two years later.
But having kids only seemed
to increase the friction
between Susan and Josh.
She would be wanting
to put them to bed.
She would even go so far
as to get them in bed,
and then he would get mad and
tell them to get out of bed
and not do what mom
told them to do.
Where did Josh get
these parenting ideas?
I'm sure from my dad.
KEITH MORRISON: More and
more influence from dad,
said Jennifer.
Josh started talking on
the phone with my dad a lot.
He would spend multiple
hours, multiple times a week
on the phone with him.
And Susan would complain to
me about how Josh would just
become unbearable to live with.
It was really obvious to
her that my dad was trying
to drive a wedge between them.
KEITH MORRISON: It
seemed to be working.
Jennifer shared
something with us
she has never made
public before.
Excerpts of emails from Susan.
Did they contain hints
of what was coming?
In one of them, she
describes her attempts
to rekindle romance with Josh.
"I've tried the
dates thing with him
and it goes to negative
or no conversation,
or it's an obligation to
him that he seems to hate."
I think it's easy to say
that Josh learned from his dad
how to treat women.
KEITH MORRISON: And then
there's another email
that suggests Susan was
actually afraid of him.
"Every moment I
step back and take
stock of what I'm dealing with.
It feels like a never-ending
cycle, but I'm too
afraid of the consequences--
losing my kids, him
kidnapping, divorce,
or actions worse on his part."
Why wouldn't he
just get a divorce?
Because she had an income.
She was the mom.
There was a very strong
argument that the boys
would have gone with her.
SOCIAL WORKER: And
so they believe
Josh found another
solution to his problem.
NATALIE MORALES: Coming up.
I sat on this feeling,
this gut-sinking,
terrible feeling that he
has done something to her.
NATALIE MORALES: When
"Dateline" continues.
Let's see, ALEVE is
proven better on pain
than Tylenol Extra Strength.
And last longer
with fewer pills.
So why am I still
thinking about this?
I'll take Aleve.
ALEVE.
Proven better on pain.
Our bodies perform,
thanks to our amazing cells.
Like you,
your cells get hungry.
Feed them.
With Centrum Silver.
Specially crafted
for Adults 50+.
So you can be awesome,
daily.
Centrum.
Feed your cells today.
KEITH MORRISON: December
7th, 2009, gone gray and cold
in Salt Lake City.
A Monday.
Josh and Susan were
both expected at work.
And neither one of
them had shown up,
and neither one of
them had called.
And they were supposed to
have dropped off their kids.
KEITH MORRISON: Dropped them
off at daycare, she means.
So the daycare center people
called their emergency
contact, Jennifer.
She went to Josh
and Susan's house.
It was empty.
The feeling hit me
really strongly that Josh
had done something to her.
KEITH MORRISON:
Hindsight, perhaps?
Or the insight of someone who
had grown up with Josh Powell.
I said, "You know, hon,
don't worry about this.
This is just a couple
and their kids.
They're off.
They're adults.
They'll be fine."
KEITH MORRISON: Then,
the late afternoon,
Josh suddenly showed up with
the boys, without Susan.
And I remember the
feeling I had at that time.
Which was what?
Which was, Josh
has done something.
KEITH MORRISON: Josh told a
story no one could believe.
That the previous night,
Sunday, he decided
to take the boys camping.
Left around midnight, he said.
Blew off work.
Drove almost 100 miles.
Slept in the family
van in temperatures
well below freezing.
Then drove back home
to find Susan, gone.
He said he had no idea
what happened to her.
When he came up with that
story about going camping,
I was just--
no.
I got a really sick feeling
that no, this is not good.
CROWD: (SINGING) Silent Night.
KEITH MORRISON:
And yet, they did
what they felt they should do.
They rallied around Josh.
They pleaded for
Susan's safe return.
We want to find
her, return her
to her husband and children.
KEITH MORRISON:
Within 10 days, police
declared Josh a
person of interest
in Susan's disappearance.
He stopped talking to
police and then left town.
Packed up his possessions
and his precious sons.
Left Utah to go
live in Washington
with his father, Steven.
When we spoke to
him in 2011, he told
us he interrogated his son.
Josh, you know,
the most abusive
thing that a father could
ever do is murder his wife.
You know, things like that.
I wanted to--
- You were testing him.
- I was testing him.
I wanted to see his reaction
to this kind of stuff.
And?
It was good.
I was totally satisfied with it.
I mean, to me, he passed
with flying colors.
KEITH MORRISON: As
for Susan, he said,
she had just run off with
another man, most likely.
Susan was veropen and
I would say very aggressive
in male-female relationships.
And she called the shots.
KEITH MORRISON: How
did he know that?
Steven claimed
Susan had developed
a long-standing crush on him.
Susan would come
in to my office
afteshe waxed her legs,
and she would sit there
and she would say,
"Feel my legs.
They're pretty smooth."
And so, yeah, I know.
Josh wasn't
concerned about this?
You know, I didn't
talk to Josh about it.
I mean, you know, I
just enjoyed the moment.
KEITH MORRISON: Steven enjoyed
quite a few moments with Susan,
he said.
Like when he'd
hand her the baby.
She'd come up and press
herself against my hands,
and then I'd have to pull my
hands out from between her
and Braden, just
slip away, you know.
That kind of a thing.
KEITH MORRISON: He said his
only regret was not going
a little further with her.
I mean, it's not
like I didn't enjoy
that kind of a little thing.
KEITH MORRISON: It was so
easy for him to tell stories.
Susan could not defend herself.
What he says is
not based on reality.
KEITH MORRISON: Josh's
sister, Jennifer Graves,
was a confidante of Susan.
And, of course, as
his daughter, she
already knew all about Steven.
He might have felt
these things for her.
He might have been
sexually attracted to her.
But she did not reciprocate.
KEITH MORRISON: For a very
few uncomfortable months,
she said, early
in their marriage,
Susan and Josh
lived with Steven.
They were set up
in the dining room,
so they had put up
sheets for the privacy.
And she had caught
my dad spying on her.
Did she say how
it made her feel?
Oh, she definitely
was creeped out by it.
He definitely made
her uncomfortable.
There was one incident
where they were in a car.
He said, "Would you
be willing to share?
Josh and I can just share you."
KEITH MORRISON: And
now, Susan was missing.
Josh was still a
person of interest.
Steven was telling lewd stories.
And these men had
Susan's children,
the Cox's grandchildren.
They were being raised by
the same person who had raised
Josh, and my daughter
was just a hundred
percent against them ever having
anything to do with Steve.
And here they
were in his house.
were in his house
because Josh went there,
you know, brings them there.
KEITH MORRISON:
But Josh's actions
brought other people
to his father's
house, namely the police.
In August, 2011, they arrived
with a search warrant.
We've got probable cause
to believe that there
are some items of
evidentiary value
inside the home of the Powells.
KEITH MORRISON:
They found plenty.
Evidence that might
eventually help
turn the mystery into an
incomprehensible tragedy.
But back then, there
was no way to know that.
Even as we sat down for an
extraordinary conversation
with the person of interest,
Josh Powell, himself,
no way to know then
that this conversation
would be the last one.
NATALIE MORALES: Coming up.
They're just trying
to rattle your cage.
It would seem.
Are you rattled?
I'm pretty pissed off.
NATALIE MORALES: Josh Powell in
his final television interview.
Were there hints of
what was to come?
When "Dateline" continues.
KEITH MORRISON: It
was August, 2011.
Still warm.
The night Josh
Powell came to see
us to break his long silence.
They know everything.
KEITH MORRISON: An extraordinary
conversation at the time,
even more so in hindsight.
As we spoke, the
police were searching
for evidence at his father's
house in Puyallup, Washington.
Josh seemed quite confident
they wouldn't find anything.
Well, according
to my attorney,
the less they have
on a person, the more
they basically harass a person.
So what you're suggesting
is that they're just
trying to rattle your cage.
It would seem.
Are you rattled?
I'm pretty pissed off.
KEITH MORRISON:
Josh claimed he knew
things about Susan's childhood
that her parents were hiding.
Susan's adult behavior, or at
least Steven's lewd suggestions
of her behavior,
claimed Josh, were
the result of childhood abuse.
An allegation the Coxes
dismiss as patently ridiculous.
I've known about
things that she's told me
about while she was growing up.
And you think
that's the reason
why, according to your father at
least, she would come onto him.
I don't think people are
characterizing that right.
She's a flirtatious person.
I hate to tell you Josh
that others who have seen
that interview with your
father have sort of gone,
"Ew, that's totally
inappropriate."
A, to behave that way.
And then, B, to
even talk about it.
Do you ever get that
sense from hearing
him describe these things?
Well, I haven't had any real
deep conversations with him
about any of that stuff.
He hasn't told you those
things, those stories?
I mean, I was there to
see that Susan was always
proud of her legs being cleanly
waxed and how smooth they were.
She would ask
people to feel them.
I told her I thought it
was pretty inappropriate.
KEITH MORRISON: Josh was
siding with his father
against just about
everyone else.
A fateful choice it turned out.
And what you're
telling me is that,
that story, or those stories
rather, as told by your dad,
are accurate.
And the stories told by Jennifer
Graves and Susan's friends,
that Susan was horrified
by this and wanted
to get the heck away from
it as much as she could,
that those stories are lies.
That's right.
So, on that night
in December, 2009,
when you went out to
the desert with the kids
to go camping, what
happened to Susan?
I think that
Susan simply left.
"Simply left."
I mean, just at midnight,
1 o'clock in the morning
just, "I've had enough.
I'm out of here."
Was she angry those days?
Nope.
Was she distressed?
Did she continue to
assert that she loved you?
Yeah.
And, God knows, she must
have loved your children.
Yeah.
And yet, she, at
midnight or 1 o'clock
or 2 o'clock in the morning
that night in December,
got up out of her bed
and went downstairs
and got on a bicycle
or something,
or walked, and simply left.
And has never, you know,
hasn't even sent you a note
to suggest she's still alive.
Is that what's happened?
I don't know what's
happened to her.
I don't know where she is.
It's the genuine
belief, obviously,
of a good many
people who have been
following this strange
saga, that you killed her.
That's the allegation that
a lot of people believe.
What can you say to them to
make them change their minds?
I've never hurt my wife.
I've never, never hurt her.
KEITH MORRISON: And
still he claimed
Susan's parents were out to get
him, to take his children away.
They started to try
to say that my sons are
in an emotionally--
some kind of emotional danger
from being in my custody.
And that's a completely
unfair statement.
KEITH MORRISON: And that's why
he did what he did, he said,
when he and the boys encountered
Chuck Cox at a hardware store
a few months after
Susan disappeared.
He said that he wanted
to hug my children.
I said, "No, you may not."
Those are his grandchildren,
just as they're your children.
I mean, shouldn't
a grandfather be
able to hug his grandchildren?
He should not be using
them as pawns in the media.
I love my sons
more than anything.
I put them first.
I put my family first.
KEITH MORRISON: Words that
now ring horribly false,
of course, as do these
about his missing
wife and their two young sons.
What do you tell them about her?
I just tell them that we
don't know where she's at.
Do they understand?
How much of it do
they understand?
I think they
understand quite a bit.
KEITH MORRISON: Indeed
it now seems they did.
And that too would play a
role in what was coming.
Do you worry that
somebody will charge
you with a crime
that will prevent
you from being with them?
Nope.
You don't think
that's going to happen?
Nope.
What makes you so sure?
Because I never did
anything that someone would
be able to charge me with.
I never hurt Susan.
And I had nothing to do
with her disappearance.
KEITH MORRISON: Did he
know how few believed him?
In the end it hardly mattered
because when police entered
the secret places in
his father's house,
they found evidence
of crimes, all right.
Not the crimes they
were looking for,
but enough to push Josh
Powell to the brink.
NATALIE MORALES: Coming up.
There are some videos
and pictures of Susan.
Somebody was hiding and shooting
through curtains and doors.
NATALIE MORALES:
Family secrets emerge
when "Dateline" continues.
That rocking chair would look
great in our new house.
Ahh, New house, eh?
Well, you should definitely see
how GEICO
could help you save on
homeowners insurance.
Nice tip. I'll give you two
bucks for the chair.
Two?! That's a Victorian
antique!
All right, how much for the
recliner, then?
Wait wait... how did that get
out here?
That is definitely not for sale!
Is this a yard sale?
If it's in the yard then it's...
for sale.
Oh, here we go.
GEICO. It's easy to switch
and save
on homeowners and renters
insurance.
Needles.
Essential for pine trees,
but maybe not for people
with rheumatoid arthritis.
Because there are options.
Like an "Unjection™".
XELJANZ XR.
A once-daily pill
for adults with moderate
to severe RA
for whom methotrexate
did not work well enough.
XELJANZ XR can reduce pain,
swelling
and further joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ XR can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes
fatal infections and cancers,
including lymphoma
have happened.
As have tears in the stomach
or intestines,
serious allergic reactions,
low blood cell counts,
higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels.
Don't start XELJANZ XR
if you have an infection.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before
and while taking XELJANZ XR,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you've been
somewhere fungal infections
are common and if you have had
TB, hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Needles.
Fine for some things.
But for you, one pill a day
may provide symptom relief.
Ask your doctor about
LJANZ XR.
An "Unjection™".
Charlie, there's
a cave over there.
KEITH MORRISON: When we met
Josh Powell in Puyallup,
Washington, he
and his dad Steven
invited us to join
them and Charlie
and Braden on a family outing.
It was summer, 2011.
JOSH POWELL: All right, come on.
KEITH MORRISON: And a
casual observer might never
have guessed the
circumstances that
brought these two strange men
and two little boys together.
The kids appeared normal, happy.
But of course, by then, for
more than a year and a half
they'd been missing
someone very dear to them--
their mother, Susan Powell.
And Susan's parents
were sure Josh knew
exactly what happened to her.
When did you first think
that Josh killed Susan?
Probably when he came up with
this "I went camping" routine.
KEITH MORRISON: But
there was not yet
enough evidence to charge him.
And then, as Josh and
I talked that evening
at the end of August, the
police raided his father's house
looking for more.
And they did find evidence, but
not at all what they expected.
Well, we discovered
a lot of computers
and a lot of material.
KEITH MORRISON: Ed Troyer of
the Pierce County Sheriff's
Department describing
what was seized
from Steven Powell's home.
There was some child
pornography in there,
and there were some voyeuristic
pictures and videos.
KEITH MORRISON: And not just
filth dug up from the internet,
but rather material someone
had filmed himself, in secret.
That someone, said
Troyer, was Steven Powell.
Pictures and videos that
were taken from his house
into the neighbor's
house of little girls
using bathroom, showers, shot
right from his own window.
KEITH MORRISON: Steven was
arrested, hauled off to jail,
and charged with 14
counts of voyeurism
and one count of possessing
child pornography, a felony.
I've been asked to plead not
guilty related to all charges.
KEITH MORRISON: This was the
same Steven Powell, remember,
who claimed his daughter-in-law
Susan had a serious crush
on him before she disappeared.
When he said it, it sounded
like an old fool's fantasy.
Now it turned out there
was evidence the fantasy
had a very dark undercurrent.
Because there was another
face, a familiar one, in Steven
Powell's homemade porn stash.
Tell me about the
discovery of the videos
involving Susan Powell.
There are some videos
and pictures of Susan
that were obviously
taken without her consent
or her knowledge.
Somebody was hiding
and taking them,
shooting through
curtains and doors
and taking pictures of her.
KEITH MORRISON: It had to have
happened early in the marriage
when Susan and Josh, strapped
for cash, moved in with Steven
for a while.
And, you know, even
though he said that she was
interested in him, we believe
that's all one big fantasy,
and she absolutely despised him.
KEITH MORRISON: The charges
brought against Steven Powell
in 2011 were ugly enough.
But before long, they set in
motion something much bigger--
a full-on battle for control
of Charlie and Braden.
We were able to take the
kids out of the residence
until an investigation was
done, and the kids were
placed with Susan's parents.
KEITH MORRISON: Susan's
parents, Chuck and Judy Cox,
in Josh and Steven's world--
the enemy.
I had Braden in the back,
it was before preschool,
and we're driving and
he says, "Grandpa,
you need to change your name."
Well, why?
My name's Charles Cox.
He says, "Yeah.
Charles Cox is a bad
person, and so you
need to change your name."
Who says Charles
Cox is a bad person?
"Oh, my daddy."
KEITH MORRISON: Josh
had done everything
he could to keep Chuck and
Judy away from his sons.
Now they had the upper hand.
My clients believe it is
very harmful for these children
to have been in the home of
Steven Powell who was deeply
involved with pornography.
KEITH MORRISON: At this
hearing that September,
Josh Powell represented
himself in family court.
Denied any knowledge of his
father's alleged crimes.
Promised to keep the
boys away from Steven,
should the elder Powell
somehow make bail.
But here you could almost
see Josh unraveling.
I am a fit and
qualified father.
I am the natural father.
I love my sons.
And the manner in which they--
[exhales loudly]
The manner in which
they were behaving
leads me to believe that
the irreparable harm that
is occurring to my sons
is having taken them out
of the stable and happy home.
KEITH MORRISON: But then a
prosecutor told the judge
that so far, only a small
portion of the evidence
had been examined.
And while Josh Powell
hadn't been charged yet,
he still might be.
Mr. Powell is a subject
of that investigation,
and that's the concern
that the department has.
KEITH MORRISON: So
Josh lost that round
and lost the ones that followed,
including the very last one.
The final defeat came
when the judge ordered
that the boys could
stay with the Coxes
for at least six more months.
So you got that
favorable ruling.
Favorable ruling.
A very good day.
Except Josh is
still not arrested.
Our daughter's still missing.
KEITH MORRISON: But
those facts might
have changed too with a second
ruling from the judge that day.
She ordered Josh
Powell to undergo
a psychosexual evaluation.
Why?
Because, according to
Utah investigators,
some images had been found
on a computer in his home
back in 2009, the year
Susan disappeared.
It was cartoons.
The cartoons and
the animation are
of adults and kids having sex.
KEITH MORRISON: And
Josh's evaluation
was to include a polygraph
test, a lie detector.
He had lost the
custody of the kids,
he had to undergo
a lie detector.
And what's he
going to tell them?
And if they ask about Susan,
with a lie detector on--
Which they would have.
Which they would have, he's
not going to be able to lie.
I just saw that as,
this is going to be--
he has no way he's going
to get through this.
The trap was really
closing in around him.
Yeah.
He's feeling really closed in.
KEITH MORRISON: And, if
that wasn't pressure enough,
there was this too.
Rumors that Charlie
and Braden were
getting pretty comfortable
with their grandparents.
That they'd started talking
about that midnight camping
trip.
NATALIE MORALES:
Just how much did
the boys know about their
mother's disappearance?
A secret is soon revealed.
Coming up.
He was explained, "Well,
mother's in the trunk."
NATALIE MORALES:
And new information
emerges about Josh's past.
There was a warning
sign, way early.
NATALIE MORALES: When
"Dateline" continues.
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50-85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
THE THREE WHAT?
THE THREE P'S?
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 54 AND I WAS
A SMOKER BUT QUIT.
ALEX, WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I'M 65, RETIRED,
AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
ALSO $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80
AND I'M ON A FIXED INCOME.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
THAT'S LESS THAN 35 CENTS A DAY.
YOU CANNOT BE TURNED DOWN
BECAUSE OF YOUR HEALTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
OPTIONS START AT $9.95 A MONTH,
PLUS, YOU GET A 30-DAY
MONEY BACK GUARANTEE.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
Emerge Restored,
Replenished,
Fortified.
Emerge everyday with Emergen-C.
Packed with B vitamins,
Electrolytes, Antioxidants,
Plus more vitamin C than
10 oranges.
Why not feel this good
every day?
Emerge and See.
KEITH MORRISON: Steven
Powell was arrested for child
pornography in September, 2011.
Josh Powell was under suspicion.
And as autumn
deepened into winter,
Chuck and Judy Cox
heard again and again,
"The arrest of Josh
Powell was next.
It could happen any day."
So they waited,
held their breath,
and took in the boys,
Charlie and Braden.
How was it, living with
those boys for the months
you had them?
How about exhausting.
Yeah.
We went to bed
exhausted every night.
But it felt good to
have the kids there.
KEITH MORRISON: The
Coxes were much stricter
disciplinarians than Josh.
They enforced early
bedtimes and regular meals.
And, according to Josh's
sister and brother-in-law,
the kids thrived.
Right after the
custody hearing,
where they were finally
in the Cox's home,
we saw them that
day and they were
withdrawn and angry and quiet.
And then two months later,
they were sitting on laps
and hugging and playing
and listening while people
read stories to them.
And they were acting
more like little boys.
We're also very
concerned for the welfare
of our grandchildren.
KEITH MORRISON: Chuck and Judy
were determined to keep them.
And as they battled
Josh in family court,
they began to turn
up new and disturbing
information about the man
who married their daughter.
They found it in the divorce
papers of his father, Steven.
Right after
Steve was arrested,
we went over to Spokane
and pulled up the record.
KEITH MORRISON: There were
disturbing allegations in there
that Josh had attempted suicide
by hanging as a teenager.
That he had threatened
his mother with a knife.
And there was this story
about Josh and Steven.
There was an incident
where Josh killed his younger
sister Alina's
hamster by smashing it
against the side of the cage.
And Josh's mother was outraged.
And Steve's response, according
to the papers there was,
"She just does not
understand teenage humor."
"Teenage humor."
Teenage humor.
And I'm going, huh?
What on earth are
you talking about?
And one of the first things
I've heard for killers
is that they abuse
animals or kill animals.
And there was a warning
signs, way early.
KEITH MORRISON: Of course,
they believed he was a killer,
had killed their daughter, even
though he hadn't been charged.
And then they say the
kids began to open up.
One of them told me one
time, I think it was Charlie,
that he hoped Mommy knew
how to camp or something
because she was out where she
needed to know how to camp.
KEITH MORRISON: And they
heard about an earlier
episode, where one
of the boys drew
a picture at his preschool.
He drew a car, two
boys, and a dad.
No mom.
The teacher asked where she was.
Well, mother's in
the trunk, you know.
And they knew who he was.
KEITH MORRISON: All the while,
even though the boys now
lived with the Coxes, they made
court-ordered visits to Josh
at the house he was renting.
A house, police now say,
he didn't really live in.
We believe that the
house was staged just
for the purpose
of the visitation
and to make himself look like
a good dad with the photos
on the wall, the kid's
stuff, the minivan
in the driveway and the garage.
And, unfortunately, it
was everything but that.
KEITH MORRISON: Where
did Josh actually live?
Steven's house.
And now that Josh seemed
in danger of losing custody
of the kids
permanently, Chuck says
he worried not about
the boys so much
but about the social worker
who took them to see Josh.
I was concerned that if she
confronted Josh in any way,
that he might hurt her.
KEITH MORRISON: Which brings
us inexorably to that Sunday,
the first time the kids
would visit Josh after he was
ordered to take the polygraph.
I got a bad
feeling about this.
And I didn't really get a bad
feeling till like Saturday.
I was thinking, you know,
maybe I should ask somebody
to have a little more
security this time,
or maybe we should
skip this visit.
KEITH MORRISON: The kids
were having fun playing.
Didn't want to go.
But, of course, there
wasn't a choice.
They had to go.
I thought, "I have to get them
to go or I'm breaking a law,
and we'll get in
trouble for it."
KEITH MORRISON: And so
she jollied them into it.
I said, "You'll
do something fun.
You know, Daddy
will have a project.
You'll get to eat with Daddy.
You'll have fun."
KEITH MORRISON: No idea, of
course, about the careful plans
Josh had been making
for that visit.
NATALIE MORALES: Coming up.
When you listen to that
tape, it's almost painful.
It's excruciating.
NATALIE MORALES:
For the first time,
the 911 dispatcher shares
his story about that day.
I wish I had recognized
the urgency of the situation.
NATALIE MORALES: When
"Dateline" continues.
I thought I was managing
my moderate to severe
ulcerative colitis.
But I realized something
was missing...
me.
The thought of my
symptoms returning
was keeping me from being there
for the people
and things I love most.
So, I talked to my doctor
and learned
HUMIRA can help get, and keep,
UC under control
when other medications haven't
worked well enough.
And it helps people achieve
control that lasts
so you could experience few or
no symptoms.
HUMIRA can lower your ability to
fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have
happened;
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like symptoms
or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if you have
an infection.
Be there for you, and them.
Ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA, control is
possible.
Bottom line is,
moms love that Land o' Frost
Premium sliced meats
have no by-products.
[CONFERENCE PHONE] Baloney!
[CONFERENCE PHONE]
Has joined the call.
Hey Baloney here.
I thought this was a
no by-products call?
Land O' Frost Premium.
A Slice Above.
I thought this was a
no by-products call?
Welcome back to "Dateline."
I'm Natalie Morales.
Time was running
out for Josh Powell.
Little Charlie and
Braden were starting
to open up about the night
their mother disappeared.
And meanwhile, a judge ordered
Josh to take a polygraph.
But first, he planned
to see his boys,
and who could have
predicted what a dark
turn those plans would take.
Now, to Keith Morrison, with
the conclusion of "A Family's
Story."
KEITH MORRISON: He was a
person of interest in Susan
Powell's disappearance.
The target of a relentless
police investigation.
His contacts with his two sons
had been reduced by court order
to a few hours twice a week.
Rumors of an imminent
arrest swirled around him.
And Josh Powell was
preparing to strike back.
Hear what police have pieced
together of his final days.
On February 4th,
2012, Josh deposited
his children's toys and
clothing in a charity drop box
near his house.
At 11:32 AM he
walked into a bank
where he withdrew $7,000 in cash
and transferred thousands more,
police believe, to his sister
who was still close to him.
At 1:30 PM he arrived
at this storage unit.
Here, police say, he
spent an hour and a half
going through
Susan's belongings.
Then, back at his
minivan, he drove 10 miles
out of town to
this landfill where
he dumped the bundle of
material from the storage unit.
That evening he walked
into this department store,
purchased two five-gallon gas
cans and a pack of Sterno--
the stuff you use
to keep food hot.
Then he went to a gas
station to fill those cans.
The next morning,
Sunday, Josh composed
emails to family members.
Most just said, "I'm sorry.
Goodbye."
At 10:30 he called his
sister Alina's cell phone.
JOSH POWELL (ON
RECORDING): Hello.
This is Josh.
And I'm-- I'm calling
to say goodbye.
I am not able to
live without my sons.
And I'm not able
to go on anymore.
I'm sorry to everyone I've hurt.
Goodbye.
KEITH MORRISON: His
alarmed sister called 911.
ALINA POWELL: I think
my brother might
be in trouble or something.
911 OPERATOR: What's going
on with your brother?
ALINA POWELL: He is--
I don't know.
He's sending weird emails.
He's saying goodbye and stuff.
KEITH MORRISON: And then, Josh
doused the house with gasoline.
Prepared the axe he
would use on the boys
before he lit the match.
Around noon, the social worker
brought Charlie and Braden for
their court-ordered visitation.
Josh grabbed the boys, pulled
them inside, locked her out.
At 12:08 she made her
first call to 911.
SOCIAL WORKER: Hey.
I'm on a supervised visitation
for a court-ordered visit,
and something really
weird has happened.
The kids went into the
house and the parent--
the biological parent,
whose name is Josh Powell--
will not let me in the door.
What should I do?
KEITH MORRISON: And
the operator kept
her on the line
answering questions
for nearly seven minutes.
911 OPERATOR: Date of birth?
SOCIAL WORKER: I don't know.
He's about 39.
911 OPERATOR: How tall?
SOCIAL WORKER: Um,
5' 10", 150 pounds.
911 OPERATOR: Hair color?
SOCIAL WORKER: Brown.
911 OPERATOR: Did you
notice what he was wearing?
SOCIAL WORKER: No, I didn't
notice what he was wearing.
KEITH MORRISON: And finally.
911 OPERATOR: All right.
We'll have somebody
look for you there.
SOCIAL WORKER: OK.
How long will it be?
911 OPERATOR: I
don't know, ma'am.
They have to respond to
emergency life-threatening
situations first.
The first available deputy--
SOCIAL WORKER:
Well, this could--
this could be life-threatening.
He went to court on
Wednesday and he--
he didn't get his kids back.
And this is really--
I'm-- I'm afraid
for their lives.
KEITH MORRISON:
Deputies were alerted
by dispatch at 12:16 PM.
It was flagged as
a routine call.
And at that moment, 911 lit
up with multiple reports
of an explosion and fire.
[phone ringing]
911 OPERATOR: 911.
What are you reporting?
MALE CALLER: I just
had a house explode.
[phone ringing]
FEMALE CALLER: The house just
blew up and it's on fire.
[phone ringing]
911 OPERATOR: What
are you reporting?
FEMALE CALLER: I believe, fire.
911 OPERATOR: Where?
KEITH MORRISON: The social
worker who delivered the boys
to Josh was back on the phone.
SOCIAL WORKER: He
exploded the house.
911 OPERATOR: Do you know
if anyone's in the house?
SOCIAL WORKER: Yes.
There was a man
and two children.
I just dropped off
the children and he
wouldn't let me in the door.
KEITH MORRISON: Chuck Cox
heard the news from a friend
who had seen it on Facebook.
And when I got there, there
were police cars, fire trucks.
And I went to the line and
the house was smoldering.
And I still didn't believe it.
KEITH MORRISON:
And with the horror
and disbelief came questions.
Could this have been foreseen?
Could Josh's evil plan
somehow had been derailed?
I feel strongly that
the judge did everything
possible to protect the boys.
Josh did it.
And I truly believe that when
someone's committed to doing
something this horrific,
there is nothing
anybody can do to stop them.
He was going to do it.
KEITH MORRISON: But could
the children have been
rescued in those final moments?
Is someone to blame?
Oh, it was horrible.
I mean, this has
been a nightmare.
KEITH MORRISON: Fingers have
been pointed at this man--
Dave Loverack.
He's the 911
dispatcher who caught
the initial call that day.
DAVE LOVERACK:
What's the address?
KEITH MORRISON: Just
one of thousands
in his 18 years on the job.
To hear how clumsy
and faltering I sounded.
SOCIAL WORKER: The visit
is with Josh Powell.
DAVE LOVERACK: And
who supervises?
SOCIAL WORKER: And
he's the husband that--
I supervise.
DAVE LOVERACK: So you supervise
and you're doing the visit?
SOCIAL WORKER: Yeah.
I supervise--
DAVE LOVERACK: You
supervise yourself?
SOCIAL WORKER: I
supervise myself.
I'm the supervisor here.
DAVE LOVERACK: Wait a minute.
If it's a supervised visit,
you can't supervise yourself.
It's almost painful because
you know what's going to happen
when you're listening to it.
But at the time, you didn't
know what was going to happen.
DAVE LOVERACK: That's right.
But as you listen to it
now, what does it do to you?
Oh, it's excruciating.
It's painful to listen to.
DAVE LOVERACK: And
the dad's last name?
SOCIAL WORKER: Powell.
I was aware of
Josh Powell's story,
but I didn't associate his name.
And so, his name was
not resonating with me.
DAVE LOVERACK: Two Ls
at the end of Powell?
SOCIAL WORKER: Yes.
Realizing what
we all know now,
I wish I had recognized the
urgency of the situation.
You're all in a
position which was,
nobody could have imagined.
Right.
Because you don't automatically
default to the notion
that the person you're
dealing with is a psychopath.
It's difficult when one goes
south on you like this one did.
The Coxes don't blame
Dave Loverack, not at all.
And they've worked
hard to stay calm,
even after the loss
of their grandsons,
along with Josh and whatever
he may have known about Susan.
I think he was very
selfish, and that's
why he took the kids.
[sighs]
If he couldn't have them,
no one could have them.
I would have
appreciated it if he
had left a note telling us
where Susan was or something,
you know.
Maybe the point was
not to tell anyone.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm sure he wants
for us to never find her.
He's still mad
at us, you know.
And mad at us because we
won't give up on our daughter,
finding our daughter.
KEITH MORRISON: Investigators
have not given up either.
They searched that storage
unit of Josh's and recovered
a comforter among
Susan's belongings.
Preliminary tests indicated
blood stains on it.
And Chuck Cox believes
there is still one person
who can answer his questions.
His dad knows something.
His dad had some part in this.
KEITH MORRISON: Police
have named Steven
Powell a person of interest.
Though he was far away
when Susan disappeared,
they have questions.
Did he goad Josh into something?
Did he devise or
assist a cover up?
Did his words help cause this?
A police source say they
grilled Steven relentlessly.
His response was silence.
And the parents of
a sunny girl will
never stop searching for her.
Will never stop hurting.
And yet--
We could be mad at Josh
and we could be mad at Steve.
It's not anger, it's sadness.
But there's hope.
We believe that they're safe in
another life with the Heavenly
Father who knows what happened.
And it will all be better,
so we have that hope.
In 2012, Steven
Powell was convicted
on 14 counts of voyeurism and
sentenced to 2 and 1/2 years.
He returned to prison in 2016
for a five-year sentence on
a child pornography conviction.
He has since been released.
Meanwhile, after an
investigation spanning
more than three years and
11 states, police in Utah
have halted their
search for Susan Powell.
That's all for this
edition of "Dateline."
I'm Natalie Morales.
Thanks for joining us.s.
[theme music]]
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY
VISIT NCICAP.ORG]