hear.
There's another thing:
Edith inherits Gregson's
publishing company.
CLARKSON:
There is no drug,
no electric shock
that will achieve what you want.
If the clerk in York remembers
selling me a return ticket
to London...
...I'm a dead man.
"Downton Abbey,"
tonight on Masterpiece.
National funding for
Masterpiece is provided by...
♪ ♪
Viking River Cruises,
proud sponsor of Masterpiece.
LINNEY:
Additional funding is provided
by The Masterpiece Trust.
And by others.
A complete list is available
from PBS.
And by contributions to your PBS
station from viewers like you.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
(bell rings)
Gracious, Mama.
It's not like you
to meet a train.
My dear, I'm taking you
straight to the house.
We'll go back and change
and return for dinner.
Do we know what time
she left yesterday?
Well, no, not precisely.
The rest of us were
at the point-to-point.
We heard
when we got back.
So what are we going
to say now?
I've been awake
the whole night.
There's only one thing
we can say.
We have to tell Cora.
Well, isn't that rather
a betrayal?
If anything happens to Edith
and Cora learns later
we knew all along,
she would never forgive us.
And I wouldn't blame her.
You see, as a mother,
it is her right.
But you don't plan
to tell Robert?
He is Edith's father.
He's a man.
Men don't have rights.
They telephoned
Lady Rosamund last night.
She's on the way here now.
It seems very hard
they should have guests staying
and more coming for dinner
with this going on.
I suppose they couldn't
put them off
without telling them why.
It'll make
for a funny evening.
We still don't know anything.
Well, we know she's
in London.
The station master said
she bought a ticket
for King's Cross.
But where can she
be hiding?
It seems a terrific imposition
for us to be here.
Should we just leave?
Why?
We've got Dicky Merton,
the Sinderbys and their son
arriving at any minute.
We could put them off.
Please don't.
They're looking forward to it
awfully.
You mean you are.
I don't think
we should.
We have to give
the impression
that Edith has simply
gone away to stay somewhere.
How terribly worrying
this is for you.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, why the song
and dance?
Edith's gone away,
so what?
We three should go for a walk
and leave them to talk.
Tony can be
our guide.
He must know the gardens
pretty well by now.
ROBERT:
Can you shed any light?
I've been racking my brains.
VIOLET:
Maybe we should
take some air.
I think we might
emulate the others
and let Cora
show us the garden.
I'm not sure
what good that'll do.
When I say we need some air,
we need some air.
Cora?
CORA:
If it's what you want.
Mary, you can manage
the children
when they get here?
Of course.
There's a person downstairs,
m'lady.
A Mrs. Drewe
from Yew Tree Farm.
She's very anxious
to see you.
CORA:
Oh, well...
You'd better show her
into my sitting room.
I'm sorry, Mama.
You go ahead without me.
I can take you for a walk
if you like.
Why would I want to walk?!
I'm going in to change.
I'll sneak upstairs
so I don't disturb them.
See you at dinner.
Not if I see you first.
I don't understand.
You're so well suited
and you're much more
relaxed with her
than you are with Mary.
Yes.
You must admit it's odd.
When Mary's trying
to break it off
and Mabel's dying
for love of you.
I know, but you see,
I can't break it off with Mary.
Not now.
Why not?
Well, I won't explain it,
but suffice to say,
it wouldn't be honorable.
You are an old dear
if you think I don't know
what you're talking about.
But isn't it up to Mary?
It's not what she wants.
Not really.
Did she look like
a woman today
trying to rid herself
of a suitor?
You're muddling
her instinct,
which is to hold
every man in thrall,
and her wish,
which is to break up.
I'm not convinced.
I wish you would be,
for everyone's sake.
Who was that letter from?
Mr. Brook.
He's got a new job
in Salford,
so he doesn't want
to renew the lease.
We need to find
another tenant, damn it.
Don't be ungrateful.
I bless your mother every day
for leaving us that house.
When you have property,
you have choices.
So what should we do?
After he's gone,
let's ask for time off together,
go down and see what condition
he's left it in.
Then we can plan.
Why are you smiling?
Because whenever
I see a problem,
you see only possibilities.
(knock at door)
May we come in?
Of course.
You've come back early.
Yes.
We rather wanted
to catch you in private
for a little chat.
Before the evening begins.
Very well.
Thank you, Baxter.
Did you both know?
Mrs. Drewe told me
Rosamund knew.
You went to see
the child with Edith.
Yes.
And you never thought to tell me
that I have a third grandchild?
Edith didn't want me to.
I suppose
this makes sense
of that bewildering trip
to Switzerland.
Well, what else
was I to do?
She wouldn't
get rid of it.
Get rid of it?
It was her idea.
But she wouldn't go through
with it in the end.
And what did you know?
Well, not quite as much.
I knew why they were
in Switzerland.
I thought she'd left
the baby there.
That was the idea.
Edith didn't stick to it.
And you never thought
to involve me, her own mother?!
You, Rosamund, you looked
at that little girl
and you never thought
it was my business, too?!
W-well, we wanted
to contain it,
to make as little
noise abroad
as possible.
So what
changed?
What tipped her over the edge
and into running away?
Well, I suppose we all knew
Mr. Gregson was dead,
but the confirmation must
have been very upsetting.
ROSAMUND:
And Mrs. Drewe
was being difficult.
Clearly, the child couldn't
stay there indefinitely.
So we thought...
What did you think?
That it would be
better and safer
if the girl
were sent abroad.
To Switzerland again,
I suppose?
Switzerland.
Or France.
They have wonderful
schools there
that'll take a child
almost from birth.
Well, now we have it!
Edith was told her child
would be taken away.
Are you going to say
anything to Robert?
No.
I agree with one thing:
the secret
is not ours to tell.
Somehow,
we must find Edith,
and we must hear from her
what she wants.
M'lady?
I'm sorry to bother you.
What is it, Mrs. Hughes?
It may have slipped
your mind, m'lady,
but do you remember
I gave you a train ticket
when we came to London
for Lady Rose's ball?
It was a return ticket
that I found in the pocket
of Mr. Bates' overcoat?
MARY:
Of course I remember.
MRS. HUGHES:
I don't suppose you put it
anywhere for safekeeping?
Why?
Because we were wrong.
Far from proving
that Mr. Bates went to London
on the day Mr. Green died,
it proved he didn't.
He bought the ticket in York,
but changed his mind,
and that's why it was
never given in.
So it was proof
of his innocence,
not his guilt?
That's about the size of it.
I'm afraid I burnt it,
Mrs. Hughes.
Atticus!
Hello.
Lord and Lady Sinderby.
Good evening, Rose.
Oh, you know my cousin?
Of course.
We were in awe
of your courage yesterday.
Well, courage
or foolhardiness.
Come and see
Mama and Papa.
To be honest, we're
in the middle of rather a drama,
which I'll tell you about,
but you mustn't let on.
Our first secret.
This is cold
so it can go up now,
but cover it
'til it's served.
Shall we work on Vanity Fair
when you're finished tonight?
I don't know.
Well, I'll ask you later.
Lord Merton's arrived,
so everyone's here.
I'll announce it
when you're ready.
I will be
by the time you say it.
You're very glum.
Am I?
Oh, don't tell me
your enthusiasm for learning
is drying up.
Maybe.
Have you read
the papers lately?
I wish I had the time.
Mr. MacDonald seems to limp
from crisis to crisis.
They were going to do so much
when they came in.
The first Labour government!
And now, I doubt
if they'll last the year.
Don't take it personally.
But I do.
When I think about it,
it seems to me
that we're trapped,
held fast in a system
that gives us no value
and no freedom.
Oy, speak for yourself.
I am... I do.
And now I'm wondering,
is it worth it,
me trying to better myself?
What's the point?
That's it--
they're coming in.
Miss Baxter.
I'm afraid you think
I've got you both into trouble.
I don't know what you mean.
Yes, you do.
I said I had no proof.
I gave them nothing
that would stand up.
Why did you have
to say anything?
I was in a difficult position.
So now you've put us in one.
I'm very sorry.
I am, truly.
I have to clean some shoes.
Are you enjoying
Yorkshire?
Well, first, we and Yorkshire
have to get used to each other.
But you haven't come up against
too many impassable barriers?
Lord Grantham, we both know
what we're up against.
Happily, we're used to it.
Well, you won't have
any trouble with us.
Lady Grantham's father
was Jewish.
That isn't always
a guarantee of tolerance,
so it's a relief
to hear you say it.
Atticus seems to be
very taken with your niece,
and I must say...
(laughs)
I find her quite charming.
Does Lord Sinderby approve?
Well, you know,
he needs time
to settle into things.
Your mother never
considered converting?
I don't believe so.
Was it difficult
having a different religion
from your father's?
Not that I recall.
But you're not
ashamed of him?
Lord Sinderby, I would point out
that we never changed our name.
Hmm.
It was my grandfather's
decision.
I thought of changing it back,
but the family felt
they were English now,
and they wanted to stay English.
Have you decided at last
whether you're leaving?
"At last"
is the right phrase.
But I want to make sure
I do the right thing.
I don't want to disrupt
Sybbie's life
and then regret it.
You know they all
want you to stay?
That only makes it
more difficult.
Lord Grantham was saying
that Gregson left Lady Edith
his publishing company.
Yes, that's right.
Then shouldn't someone
telephone the office?
Won't she go there?
They must know
where to find her.
Of course.
How clever you are.
Am I?
It seems rather
obvious to me.
ROSE:
Your mother and Robert
are hitting it off.
She's not the problem.
Oh?
My father's the tough nut.
My people are
the other way round.
My father's a darling
and my mother's the nut.
Then we shall crack them
against each other.
(laughing)
It's strange how some people
get married and married,
and we can't
manage it once.
Dogs barking and wrong trees
spring to mind.
Tony, I'm sorry
if you feel
I'm tracking you
round the country,
but I can't give up just yet.
We could be so very happy
if you'd let us.
And I won't be
if I don't?
I remember my mother telling me
that in the end,
happiness is a matter
of choice.
Some people choose
to be happy,
and others select a course
that leads only to frustration
and disappointment.
And I am one
of the latter?
I terribly hope not.
For my sake.
(guests fall silent)
I have a little announcement.
Are you sure?
I am.
You might like to know
that Lord Merton and I
have decided that we
should get married.
(guests respond happily)
How lovely.
Well, this calls
for a toast.
I give you Mrs. Crawley,
or should I say
the future Lady Merton?
ALL:
The future Lady Merton.
Naturally, it was the last thing
I ever thought would happen.
(laughter)
I forced her into it.
He wooed me into it, and I'm
terribly pleased he did.
Well...
What's the matter, Granny?
Oh, nothing.
Why should there be?
I thought you looked
rather bleak.
I'm just worried about Edith.
I can't think why.
My dear, a lack of compassion
can be as vulgar
as an excess of tears.
Ah, Daisy.
Have you decided?
Shall we discuss the vices
of Miss Becky Sharp?
I'm tired.
I'm going up.
Good night, Mrs. Patmore.
What's that about?
She had such hopes
of the Labour government.
She feels let down.
But she mustn't give up.
I don't recall you
being this keen
when Miss Bunting
was teaching her.
I wouldn't interfere
with a professional,
but now that she's gone,
I'd like to help
if I can.
Sounds to me as if you've
missed out on your vocation.
Tell Daisy.
Perhaps you can change her mind.
She wouldn't listen to me.
Well spotted.
What about Mr. Mason?
Funnily enough, Mr. Barrow
might be right for once.
How do we get him
to speak to her?
Let me think on it.
CORA:
I'm sorry if I seem
distracted,
but I'm truly so happy
for both of you.
I thought I'd give a dinner
so she can meet my sons.
Well, she has met
Larry before.
Let's hope she's forgotten.
Why don't we
do it here?
We could invite Granny
and everyone.
You are my godfather
and Isobel's the grandmother
of my child.
Oh, please let's.
It seems only
right, Mama.
Of course,
if you'd like.
Well, that'd be very kind.
A signing of the bond
between our families.
I wish we didn't know
the anguish
lurking behind
this jolly evening.
You love other people's
secrets.
Not these days.
There are lots of things
I don't want to know.
Such as?
I don't want to know
what you see in Mary.
I just want you back.
I do admire you
for saying that.
I'd rather be happy than proud.
I can't tell you
why I can't leave Mary.
But you'd understand
if I did.
Just promise me
it's a struggle.
More than you know.
We must go,
but it's been such fun.
I hope you'll come to us
next time.
We should love it.
I suppose now we just have
to wait and see what happens.
LORD SINDERBY:
There's no need to hurry them
into anything.
They're both very young.
Well, I would be delighted
if something were to come of it.
Good night, Lady Grantham,
Lady Rosamund.
The door, please,
Molesley.
I'm afraid your plan of getting
Mabel here hasn't worked.
I disagree.
They're so easy
in each other's company.
Anyone can see it.
But he won't let me go.
Because you refuse
to make it clear
that you want him to.
Just as he's moving off,
you tug his strings.
Send a clear message,
and he'll go.
I promise.
What is that message?
We'll think of something.
(Rose clears her throat)
Atticus says the London office
of the magazine
must know how to get
in touch with Edith.
I thought we weren't going
to tell anyone.
He's not "anyone," is he?
Of course not.
We could ring them
tomorrow,
but maybe I should
just go there.
Mr. Aldridge is leaving.
Oh.
I'll train up
in the morning.
I'm coming with you.
I'm not going.
But I'll have a horrible day
worrying.
Trust me.
How can you imagine
I'll ever trust you again?
She doesn't mean it, Mama.
On the contrary,
it's the most honest thing
she's ever said to me.
ANNA:
Here you are.
Thank you.
Is our life
over-complicated?
In what way?
Mrs. Patmore is buying
a house up here.
Why don't we sell the London
house and do the same?
We could rent it out as long as
we want to work at Downton.
And then live in it
when we retire?
We had a dream once
of a small hotel
in the area.
And a London house,
even a little one,
would buy something
substantial up here.
I hate to say his name,
but do you feel the whole
business of Mr. Green
might be over?
For us, I mean.
Well, they seem to have
accepted the fact
that I spent the day in York,
and Miss Baxter has given them
nothing new to go on.
So we can dare to plan
our future again?
Like normal people?
Does that mean
what I hope it means?
Mr. Bates, I thought you'd
decided to believe me
when I said that device
was Lady Mary's?
I do believe you.
I don't know why
she wanted it,
but I believe you.
Well, then.
You don't suppose there's
anything wrong with us, do you?
No.
I think it takes some people
longer than others.
That's all.
What would I do without you?
Did they get away?
Just about.
The train was late,
thank heaven.
And it isn't going
to be Tony?
I don't think so.
Nor Charles?
He decided that
before I did.
Well, well.
I don't suppose your
ancient father's opinion
on these matters
carries much weight?
Afraid not,
and I've just remembered
I said I'd go
and see Granny.
So, I don't think Tony is going
to be my next son-in-law.
I don't believe he is.
Pity.
I would have been so pleased,
but there we are.
You're really not yourself,
are you, old girl?
What about you?
We don't want you to be
on your own forever, you know.
Just to pick someone who shares
the family's values.
(laughs)
Someone who feels
friendly towards us.
It's not the same thing.
No, you're right.
And I don't blame you for
the departure of Miss Bunting.
I didn't want to spend my life
in a bare knuckle fight.
But something's changed.
I feel it.
I may as well tell you:
I've written to my cousin
in Boston.
He's done well there,
and I'd like his advice.
I see.
I apologize if my bad manners
have brought this on.
No need to apologize.
I am what I am
and you are what you are.
And never the twain
shall meet?
I wouldn't say that.
I do love you all,
you know.
It'll be hard to go.
On both sides.
RECEPTIONIST:
But we have no way of knowing
if Lady Edith
will come in today.
It's already tea time,
and we close the office at 6:00.
Then we'll wait
until 6:00.
And we'll come back
in the morning,
and every day
until she either turns up
or contacts you
with her whereabouts.
It wouldn't be enough
to give her a message
that you want
to see her?
CORA:
No, it would not be enough.
You've told her,
haven't you?
You've broken your word.
No, I...
Mrs. Drewe came
to the house.
What did she want?
She felt you had
used her badly.
I confess it was
a feeling we shared.
I'm not coming back,
you know.
Let's not talk
about it here.
Come to me for dinner.
No.
Very well, then.
We'll discuss it now
in front of your new employees
and give them something
to chew on.
There is a tea room
at the end of the street.
How are you, Spratt?
Well, I hope.
Everyone has their
troubles, m'lady.
Oh, dear.
Spratt has been helping
to train my new maid, Denker.
I'd say she takes
after the dachshund, m'lady.
In what way?
She's quite untrainable.
Spratt.
Will there be anything else,
your ladyship?
(sighs)
Sounds like trouble to me.
Are you certain Denker's
worth it?
Oh, you must put dinner
on Friday into your diary.
That's when Dicky Merton's
coming with his sons.
Yes, I wonder if it is
a good idea.
Isobel's got to meet them
sometime.
And Larry won't make trouble
for Tom again.
Not with Sybil dead.
Let us hope not.
Granny, I know why you're
finding this difficult.
Do you?
Yes.
But you mustn't give in to it.
Give in to what?
Isobel's always been
your protégé.
She looks up to you,
and you have kept her
from harm in return.
Have I?
Yes, so of course
it's difficult
that she is to take her place
among the leaders of the county.
Oh, why?
Why is it difficult?
You needn't pretend.
Your positions have changed.
You, the widow
in the Dower House.
Isobel, a great lady
presiding
over a great house.
But you simply have to be
bigger than that.
Is that what you think of me?
That I care
about her change of rank?
Well, you're not exactly
pleased, are you?
No.
But that is not the reason.
Then what is?
Well, if you must know...
I've got used to having
a companion.
A friend.
You know, someone
to talk things over with.
Well, you'll still have us.
You have
your own lives,
and so you should.
But Isobel and I
had a lot in common, and...
I shall miss that.
Granny, you're quite dewy-eyed.
I never think of you
as sentimental.
Nor am I.
You've made me regret
my confidence.
Do have some cake.
And for your information,
I don't think Isobel
has ever looked up to me.
Now, we'll drop the sticks
in together, when I say.
Ready?
Go!
Where are they?
There it is!
It's me, it's me!
Now make a wish.
Darling, you know Aunt Edith
has gone to London?
Yes.
Only I was thinking.
And I wonder,
what if we were to leave here
and to go and live in a place
far away across the sea?
What would you say?
Why?
Well, because...
It might be better for us
to start a new life there.
Why?
Because...
Because I hope to God
I'm doing the right thing.
(clock chiming)
That's the stable clock.
We better get back.
I've got an idea
and I've told Mrs. Hughes,
but I want you to know it.
I could swear the train ticket
hadn't been used.
I would swear it.
What?
I saw the ticket
in Mrs. Hughes's hand
when she found it
in the coat.
It hadn't been
torn in half.
It was whole.
I saw it.
Did you indeed?
Things have moved on,
Miss Baxter.
They know Mr. Bates was
in York on that day.
I just wanted
to be helpful.
We know how you like to be
helpful, Miss Baxter.
By talking to the police
about us.
Excuse me.
I couldn't help
overhearing.
Miss Baxter
won't say it,
but she's
in a difficult position.
On the contrary.
Miss Baxter
keeps saying it.
She says nothing else.
(clears throat)
Mr. Molesley,
can you remove the baize
from the tables, please?
I'm ready to go up.
I'll come with you.
Ignore them.
I can't.
I feel sorry for them.
Then tell them why you had
to talk to the police.
I'd feel ashamed.
You're in luck.
I'm only just back.
Now, listen carefully.
Today I learned I've been posted
on a trade delegation to Poland.
Oh, some people
have all the fun.
Mmm.
I'll be gone for months.
What a shame.
Does that mean our plot
goes west?
Not necessarily.
I want you to come up
to London tomorrow.
I've some things I can't
get out of in the morning.
That doesn't matter.
I just need you from
about 7:00 on.
What for?
Mabel's given me an idea
for how to settle it
once and for all.
Just be here.
What sort of clothes?
Rags.
We're going to the Kinema.
Ring me when you get to London.
Your wish is my command.
Bye.
(gong ringing)
I'm worried about Isis.
Why? What's the matter
with her?
ROBERT:
She's not looking too clever.
Did you manage to get hold
of Mr. Stapeley?
I spoke to his wife,
my lord.
He's away until Friday.
Do you want me to try
to find someone else?
No, no.
I'll take her
down there myself
on Friday afternoon.
Has the gong been rung yet?
Just.
Why do we bother
to change?
It's you, me,
Mary and Tom.
Don't let Aunt Violet
hear you.
Where have you been?
I went to have tea
with Atticus.
We met halfway,
in Ripon.
It's getting
quite serious, then?
Fingers crossed.
But darling, you don't want
to rush into anything.
Oh, but I do.
I want to rush in
like billy-o.
Rose, it's a big thing
you're contemplating.
Bigger still because
of the circumstances.
You sound like
Lord Sinderby.
I could see
he wasn't very keen.
He doesn't want Atticus
to marry out of the faith.
He minds.
Why shouldn't he mind?
He's a very important figure
in that community.
But you're not against it,
are you?
Of course not.
Still, I think you ought
to write to your parents.
Oh, Daddy won't try
and stop me.
No, I don't believe
he will.
And Mummy hates everyone,
so what's the difference?
Even so, it's best
not to pretend
that it'll be
plain sailing.
(sighs)
No second cups, I'm afraid.
They shut in a minute.
We were just discussing
Mrs. Drewe,
whether or not she blabbed
to anyone else.
She says not.
She felt I was different
because I'm your mother.
I ought to know I have
another grandchild,
and I agree with her.
Where is Marigold now?
The hotel arranges a babysitter
when you need one.
May I see her?
I don't think so.
Not tonight.
ROSAMUND:
So what are you
going to do?
I was toying for a while
with the idea
of going to America.
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
Why is that ridiculous?
She's half American,
isn't she?
I thought I'd
drop my title
and invent a dead husband.
Then I'd be Mrs. Thing
in Detroit or Chicago,
where I wouldn't run
into anyone I knew.
So is that your plan?
I don't want the magazine
business to fall into ruin.
How could I keep an eye on it
overseas?
And I would like Marigold
to grow up English.
Then what is
the alternative?
An invented
dead husband here?
I'd never get away with it
in London.
I thought I'd make her
my orphaned godchild.
Well, I have a different plan.
I'd like you to bring her home.
No.
I won't be the County Failure.
Poor demented
Lady Edith,
who lost her virtue
and her reason.
Just listen to my plan.
The Drewes would reach
a reluctant conclusion
that they can't afford to raise
their friend's child.
You've grown so fond
of the girl,
you ask if she might join the
others in the Downton nursery.
Well, the Drewe plan
was mad enough,
but this is completely
ludicrous.
How could it
possibly work?
Papa must never know the truth.
I've thought about it,
I don't agree.
While it would take time for him
to get used to the idea,
I believe
he would make it.
No, he'd never look at me
in the same way again.
Very well.
If that's how you feel,
he doesn't have to know.
Nor Mary.
I couldn't have Mary
queening it over me.
No one has to know
who doesn't know already.
Your grandmother, Rosamund,
you and me.
Everyone else will be told
the story.
And how would we execute
this insanity?
A farmer's foster child turns up
in the Downton nursery?
People adopt babies
all the time
from all kinds
of backgrounds.
So you're going to try
and do this?
I'll telephone
Mr. Drewe tonight
when we get back
to Belgrave Square
and I'll ask for his help.
And what about his wife?
Let him manage her.
Edith and I will go home
tomorrow.
I'll ask Mr. Drewe to meet
the train and take Marigold.
Then we'll discuss
the Drewes' situation
with the family,
and at last,
Edith will fetch the girl
and bring her back to the house
in broad daylight.
Time to call it a day, ladies.
I couldn't agree more.
And one for you,
Mr. Molesley.
Oh!
I'm going up
with Lady Mary this afternoon,
but only for the night.
You didn't have
much warning.
ANNA:
I know, but
something's come up.
I suppose there's no point
in you looking in at the house.
Not this time.
Leave it 'til
Mr. Brook's left
and we can both go.
Oh, it's an invitation
from Mr. Mason.
What, my Mr. Mason?
Your Mr. Mason.
He wants you and me
to come to the farm tomorrow
for luncheon,
if we can get the time off.
Why don't you go with them?
I'm sure her ladyship
wouldn't mind.
What's it to you?
Well, you did me a good turn
when I'd done you a bad one.
So I think you
deserve a treat.
He's right,
it would do you good.
But I've not been asked.
Mr. Mason would be glad
to see you,
but would Mr. Carson
let us go?
Oh, I think he will
if you allow me to handle it.
He won't like it
when we've got a big dinner on.
Well, just let me tell him.
After all, I'm the one
with the extra work.
And would Miss Baxter
be able to come with us?
As Mr. Barrow says.
Well, I don't see why not
as long as you're back in time.
You could go early.
I still don't understand
why he'd write to Mr. Molesley.
Well, I might have mentioned
that he's been helping you
with your books.
You know I write to him
now and then.
Can you see him?
Not yet.
CORA:
Oh, my God.
There's Mary.
What?
CORA:
There's Mr. Drewe.
What should we do?
Leave it to me.
Mr. Drewe.
Can you help my mother
with her suitcases?
My sister Mary
is on the platform.
Go to the next station
and come back.
I'll cover the cost.
Hello, come on, you.
That's it.
Come on, darling,
it's just a game.
(train whistle blows)
So!
You found her.
I did.
I don't know what
the fuss was about.
I just thought I'd like
a day or two in London.
I knew it.
I said that's all it was.
What a nonsense they made!
CORA:
Why are you here?
I'm catching the fast train
to London.
It's due any minute.
When will you be back?
I'm not sure.
Tomorrow, I think.
Don't forget
the dinner on Friday.
We have a duty to protect
Isobel from Larry Grey.
I don't think he'll try
anything, do you?
Well, have a lovely time.
I'm sure I will.
That was close.
(bell rings)
Have I met
your younger son?
I remember
the elder one.
I should think you do
after his outburst
the last time,
but Larry
was fond of Sybil
and not about to welcome
the man who'd won her.
Oh, let us hope the years since
have made him more forgiving.
I'm looking forward to it,
and I think we should make
no reference
to the earlier meeting.
How lucky I am in you.
I know it
every time you speak.
Flatterer.
I should be going.
I'll see you on Friday.
I can't wait.
Thank you so much
for my lovely tea.
Not a bit.
Spratt will see you out.
Spratt still looks
rather down in the mouth.
I'm afraid the battles with
Denker are far from resolved.
It's good to have
a moment alone
to say how much I appreciate
your kindness to Dicky.
I know you don't approve,
which makes you
all the more generous.
Thank you.
Well, it's too late
to stop it.
How is Prince Kuragin?
I haven't heard
from him lately.
Why?
Well, I was just wondering
how you were going to manage
when the Princess
finally arrives.
Will you receive her here?
Well, I'm not sure.
Since Shrimpie
hasn't found her yet,
I've got time to plan.
Ah.
Oh!
What is it now, Spratt?
I'm sorry to bother
your ladyship,
especially when you
have company.
I'm afraid I must
hand in my notice.
I have suffered
as much as anyone
can expect to suffer
in the course of their duties.
I can take no more, m'lady.
I can take no more.
(door closes)
Typical Spratt.
He's as touchy as a beauty
losing her looks.
You don't think he meant it?
Well, if he did,
he'd have given
his notice quietly
for a good reference
in return.
No, no, it is simply
a demonstration of discontent.
So you'll forgive
his outburst?
Anything rather than find
a new butler.
(laughing)
(music playing)
MARY:
Why did we have to rush out?
Now come and stand here.
I still don't understand.
You will.
Do exactly as I tell you
and you will.
Kiss me.
What?
Kiss me. Now.
Mary?
What are you doing here?
So what did you think
of the film?
There was no need
to stage a tableau.
If you'd just told me
I was allowed to walk away,
then I'd have gone.
Without any silly games.
But I did tell you, often,
and you didn't go.
Well, I'm going now.
I know, and I wish you both
such happiness, Tony,
I really do.
I don't want to hurry anyone,
but can we bring this
to an end?
I've had quite enough sentiment
from John Barrymore
and I'm starving.
Good-bye, Mary.
And good luck to you.
Well, I'm glad to have
engineered a resolution,
even if I should have
thought of it long ago.
He said we didn't need to do it,
but I know we did.
It's funny.
I feel quite sad in a way.
But not sad enough
to change my mind.
She's nice, you know.
She'll suit him very well.
Good, I'm glad.
So, what now?
Shall we find ourselves
some dinner, too?
Let's.
We'll toast
the fun we've had
and whatever the future
may bring us.
When are you off
to Poland?
I catch the boat train
on Monday.
So I'm scrambling around,
trying to get everything done.
When are you back?
Not for months,
or even a year.
You'll be married by then.
There.
You all finished?
How lovely, Daisy,
to have such a beautiful
place to come to.
Oh, she's always welcome,
is Daisy.
I've not been here enough
lately.
You've been busy, I know,
with your books.
That takes up time.
I think I'll stop it now,
so I'll be able
to visit more.
Do you think she's right to
give up her studies, Mr. Mason?
I do not!
Don't you want
to see more of me?
You know I do.
But education is power.
Don't forget that.
There's no limit
to what you can achieve
if you'll just give
a year or two
to mastering those books.
I agree, Mr. Mason.
There are millions out there
who could have done so much,
if they'd only been given
an education.
I'm one of them.
I could have made something
worthwhile of my life,
if I'd had the chance.
Don't talk as if your life
were not worthwhile,
when I know it is.
DAISY:
But I think the system's
slanted against us,
that the men in charge will
always be the men in charge.
How can you say that with
a Labour government in power?
I doubt they'll last the year.
Well, next time
when they're elected,
it'll be for longer,
and soon, a Labour government
might seem quite ordinary.
Do you think
I should stick at it?
I do.
And now we ought
to think about
getting you
back to the bus.
Let me take these.
No, no, Daisy and I
are your hosts.
Thank you.
Well, thank you.
He's made a daughter out of
his widowed daughter-in-law.
I like it when good things
come from bad.
Have you thought
of explaining to Mr. Bates
why you had to speak out?
He'd understand
if anyone would.
He's troubles enough
without burdening him with mine.
We should go.
We must be back in good time
for Mrs. Crawley's dinner.
Mr. Carson says
there was trouble
the last time Lord Merton's
elder son came to Downton.
Why? What happened?
Alfred told me if Mr. Branson
hadn't been too drunk to stand,
we'd have had fisticuffs
on the table.
Hey!
And here's me thinking life
in a great house
must be dull work.
(laughing)
Walk on.
MARY:
Do Mr. and Mrs. Drewe
really want you
to take her?
Or is it just a way
of keeping her here
until they have her back?
I don't think so.
They simply can't afford
another child.
And there aren't
any prior claims?
Apparently not.
That's why they took her
in the first place.
What did he say?
Is she carrying puppies?
Because I don't see how
that could have happened.
No, it's not that.
She's got cancer,
poor old thing.
CORA:
Oh, no!
Oh, how I hate
that word.
He said it won't
take long now.
He offered to put her down
there and then,
but I...
I couldn't quite let him.
MARY:
Oh, Papa.
I am so, so sorry.
Of course
we're stupid
to mind so much.
She probably doesn't
even know who I am
beyond the hand
that feeds her.
But even so...
CORA:
We'll keep her
right here.
This is her spot.
She'll know she's
back at home.
I suppose we can't stop
this ghastly dinner tonight?
I don't see how.
Dicky's sons
have come from London.
And Atticus
was on the same train.
No, of course
we can't put it off.
I wasn't thinking.
Why don't we say
that you're ill?
I could watch her.
I don't have to go
to the dinner.
I think you do.
To lay the ghost of the last
time Larry Grey was here.
I asked them
to bring them down early.
SYBBIE:
Hello, Daddy.
Come to Mama, darling.
Hello, my darling.
So, how should I answer?
What's this about?
The child
at the Drewes' house.
(sighs)
It seems idiotic to me.
MARY:
And me.
What about if you want
to start a family of your own?
But I dote on her.
If they send her
to some horrid orphanage,
I'd never forgive myself.
But can't you just
give them some money
so they can keep her?
I think... Mrs. Drewe
finds it too much.
It isn't only the money.
That seems a bit feeble.
Does it?
Looking at these two?
(laughs)
So should I take her?
Papa?
I leave it to your mother.
Well, I believe
we should offer
little Marigold
a home here.
Do you really, darling?
Well, then I suppose
that's settled.
(knocking)
Have all the guests
arrived?
I think so.
Oh, I should tell Mrs. Patmore
that it won't be long now.
Lady Mary was saying
Lady Edith's going to adopt
that little girl
the Drewes had taken in.
Well, I don't know
if she'll adopt her,
but she's bringing her
here to live.
Is she now?
What are these?
Oh, Mr. Carson's got a notion
he and I might buy a place
as an investment
and maybe run it
as a guest house
or rent it out.
How strange.
Mr. Bates was talking about
doing something similar.
I suppose we're all beginning
to think of a different future,
whether we want to or not.
Mr. Drewe was on the platform
the other day,
when Lady Mary and I were
waiting for the London train.
Oh, yes?
Then her ladyship
and Lady Edith arrived
and he got
into their carriage.
He helped lift their bags out,
but then he just stayed there.
In First Class?
Oh!
That'll have cost him
a pretty penny.
When the train moved off,
I thought for a moment
he had a child on his lap.
I may have been wrong...
Anna.
You shouldn't
involve yourself
in any speculation
of that sort.
The child is safe
and the child is loved,
and that's all we need
to be sure of.
ISOBEL:
I've been hearing
about Edith's plan.
How marvelous of her.
If you ask me,
it's absolutely crackers.
But Cora seems pleased.
What idea is this?
Edith has taken in
a motherless child
and is giving her
a home here.
I should have thought
an orphan
rather an uncomfortable
piece of baggage
for an unmarried woman.
ISOBEL:
You mean a man
might not want
to take the child on?
Well, I wouldn't.
Rose, have you written to your
mother about Mr. Aldridge?
I have now.
And will she approve?
Don't be disappointing,
Aunt Violet,
please.
I promise you, we both know
a difference in religion
is a big thing.
Quite right.
How would you bring up
any children, for example?
Children?
When did this happen?
(laughter)
I'm talking hypothetically.
The fact is,
most marriages that fail
founder for precisely
this kind of reason.
An irreconcilable
difference.
Or maybe they just
don't get on.
TIM:
I'd agree with Larry.
It's usually more than that.
LARRY:
Oh, it might be
different beliefs
or different
nationalities
or a huge age gap.
In the end,
they cannot see eye to eye.
I don't see
what you're getting at.
You mean to marry
Mrs. Crawley here.
She seems very nice,
and I wish you both
every happiness.
Thank you.
But that doesn't
prevent me from seeing
that the wide disparity
in class and background
may prove your undoing.
What did you say?
Only that Mrs. Crawley,
a decent,
middle-class woman
with neither birth
nor fortune,
is expecting to fill
our mother's shoes
as one of the leaders
of the county.
Is she capable of it?
Or will her inevitable failure
prove a source of misery
to them both?
ROBERT:
You know Mrs. Crawley's
late son was my heir?
What does that prove?
Everyone has distant cousins
who are fairly odd.
How dare you!
Will you go, Larry?
I had to make excuses
for your rudeness
the last time you sat
at this table.
It is tiring to think I shall be
called upon to do so again.
I know the choice of in-laws
is eccentric in this family.
You already boast
a chauffeur
and soon you can claim a Jew,
but even so...
Why don't you just
get out, you bastard!
VIOLET:
And suddenly we've slipped
into a foreign tongue.
Well.
If that is how you feel.
I do not endorse Tom's language
but that is certainly
how we all feel.
Then, Lady Grantham, good-bye.
And thank you
for a delightful evening.
(door closes)
What did you imagine?
That we would welcome you
with open arms?
He actually
called him that?
He did,
right to his face!
Mr. Molesley, please.
I think he was right
to say it.
He may have been right,
but I will not have bad language
in front of the maids.
I feel very sorry
for Mrs. Crawley.
Why should she be
humiliated?
They're leaving early.
And no wonder.
(giggling)
Mr. Molesley,
why are you down here?
Not gossiping, I hope?
Oh, no, no,
Mr. Carson, no.
Golly, what an evening.
We won't forget it
in a hurry.
Let us remember it
for two reasons.
One bad, one good.
Oh, what's the good one?
Well, I hope it is good.
I'm listening.
See, the thing is,
it occurs to me that
we're already having
to defend ourselves.
Yes.
So let's have
a real reason to.
That is,
if you feel equal to it.
I'm not going
to give you an answer
until you say it properly.
Do I have to kneel down?
Of course!
But you don't have
to stay kneeling
for very long.
Rose.
Darling Rose.
Will you marry me?
You can get up now.
Well, go on.
We ought to be serious.
The truth is that
we haven't known
each other very long,
and they're right
that there are bound
to be problems.
But the way I see it,
we both know we're going
to get married in the end.
We know we're
right together.
Yes, I suppose we do.
That's all I need to hear.
I'll telephone tomorrow
and we'll settle who tells what
to whom and when.
Oh, darling!
(door opens)
(giggling)
I'm going to wait
in the car.
Take as long as you like.
We will laugh about this
one day.
The sooner,
the better.
Good night.
Tell me it won't
change your mind.
I can't talk about this tonight,
nor for some time to come.
And I think Rose
and her young man
will take up every scrap of
attention we have for weddings.
Please don't say that.
Papa!
Larry's been sitting
in the car
since he left the dining room.
I'm just coming.
I'll say goodnight,
Mrs. Crawley.
Good night.
Don't blame Larry.
He was close to his mother
and hates the thought
of a replacement.
They both do.
You don't need
to remind me.
The boys take after their mother
in every possible way.
(giggling)
I'm going to sleep
in the dressing room tonight.
I'm not cross, I just want
to have her with me.
Stay here.
The thing is, I'm pretty sure
she won't last 'til morning
and I don't want her
to be frightened.
Then lay her here between us,
and she'll know
she has someone
who loves her very much
next to her.
Two people who love her,
and each other, very much
on either side.
I only hope I can say the same
when my time comes.
National funding for
Masterpiece is provided by...
♪ ♪
Viking River Cruises,
proud sponsor of Masterpiece.
LINNEY:
Additional funding is provided
by The Masterpiece Trust.
And by others.
A complete list is available
from PBS.
And by contributions to your PBS
station from viewers like you.
Thank you.
Visit us at pbs.org/masterpiece
to watch video
and explore features,
and follow us
on Facebook and Twitter.
Season 5 of "Downton Abbey"
is available on Blu-ray and DVD.
The companion book, A Year
in the Life of Downton Abbey,
is also available.
To order, visit shopPBS.org
or call 1-800-PLAY-PBS.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
MASTERPIECE
ONLY ON PBS
[Glasses clink]
Narrator: Tucked away
up Connecticut Avenue
sits Bistrot du Coin.
An energetic crowd
has gathered,
enjoying French classics
like steamed mussels
and steak frites.
Woman: We love the food.
We love the atmosphere.
We love the environment.
It's just...
It's just
a fantastic place.
The drinks are good.
The lights are low.
[Sizzling]
Man: It's not
sophisticated food,
but it's nice,
hearty food.
This is the thing
I would have at home.
Bon appetit.
It's a typical French bistro,
but with a different ambiance.
It's French, fun, and friendly.
That's our model.
Woman: The food is
really the best
food in town,
and it's a busy,
warm environment.
Joe Dassin: ♪ Je m'baladais
sur l'avenue ♪
♪ Le coeur ouvert à l'inconnu,
j'avais... ♪
Man: This is probably
the best place in D.C.
where you can find
great wines at a
fairly cheap price,
which is unusual.
Narrator: But it's the steamed
mussels that keep customers
coming back.
The Bistrot's secret?
You have to start with
a great quality of mussel.
We get delivery every day.
Because of the volume
we go through, nothing stays.
[People talking loudly;
music playing]
Narrator: 3 times a year,
the Bistrot kicks
into overdrive,
throws a party
you won't soon forget.
Tonight, when the clock
strikes midnight,
this year's vintage
of Beaujolais Nouveau wine
can officially be uncorked.
[Music playing]
Singer: ♪ ...in the street ♪
Felix: Tonight, we celebrate
the new one of the year,
and it's a crazy party.
It's more like a tradition that
we give back to our customer.
All year long, they come
and support us,
and with Beaujolais Nouveau,
we go crazy.
So, we give away
a lot of bottle.
I cannot tell how much,
but it's a lot.
And then we put
everybody on UBER!
[Music continues]
Narrator: To learn more
about "Neighborhood Eats,"
visit WETA.org.
Narrator: To learn more
about "Neighborhood Eats,"
LAURA LINNEY:
This is "Masterpieiece."
I desire to leave your service,
ma'am.
LINNEY:
Previously on "Victoria."
SOPHIE:
The man Joseph.