>> Dr. Phil: WARNING.
TODAY'S SHOW WILL TAKE A DEEP
DIVE INTO WHAT I CONSIDER THE
MOST HEINOUS, DESPICABLE AND
EVIL THING EVER PERPETRATED BY A
PARENT.
>> WAS MY DAD'S SEX SLAVE.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU SAID YOU WOULD
WAKE UP TO YOUR FATHER ON TOP OF
YOU.
>> WHEN I WAS 6, HE STARTED
KISSING ME.
I WAS 7 YEARS OLD.
HE STARTED SEXUALLY ABUSING ME.
MY FATHER FED ME DRUGS.
HE PUT A BAG OVER MY HEAD AND
SUFFOCATED ME.
>> Dr. Phil: AS UNIMAGINABLE AS
THIS STORY IS, YOU HAVEN'T HEARD
THE WORST OF IT YET.
MEET TATIANA.
TATIANA LEFT BRAZIL AND MOVED TO
AMERICA AT JUST 6 YEARS OLD TO
LIVE WITH HER PARENTS.
ALMOST IMMEDIATELY HER FATHER
BEGAN FORCING HER TO DO DRUGS SO
HE COULD SEXUALLY ABUSE HER AND
BEAT HER FEET BLACK AND BLUE
WITH A BAT.
AT 12 YEARS OLD TATIANA'S FATHER
PULLED HER OUT OF SCHOOL AND
SEXUALLY ASSAULTED HER EVERY
SINGLE DAY.
HE INSTALLED SECURITY CAMERAS
AND MOTION SENSORS AROUND THEIR
HOME, MAKING IT IMPOSSIBLE FOR
HER TO ESCAPE.
SHE SAYS SHE WAS TERRORIZED BY
HER FATHER WHO REGULARLY
THREATENED TO KILL HER IF SHE
EVER TOLD ANYBODY ABOUT THE
ABUSE.
THEN AT 25, AFTER 19 YEARS OF
TORTURE, SHE WAS FINALLY
RESCUED.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> RIGHT NOW I'M BROKEN,
CONFUSED AND I DON'T KNOW IF I
CAN LIVE A NORMAL LIFE.
I WAS SEXUALLY, PHYSICALLY,
EMOTIONALLY ABUSED BY MY
BIOLOGICAL FATHER.
I WAS ABUSED FOR 19 YEARS.
I WAS MY DAD'S SEX SLAVE.
ANYTHING HE WANTED, I HAD TO DO.
A LOT OF THESE PICTURES I'M
SMILING BUT I'M DYING INSIDE.
FROM WHEN I WAS 6, HE STARTED
KISSING ME DOWN THERE AND
TOUCHING ME DOWN THERE.
HE WOULD TELL ME NOT TO TELL.
HE WOULD ASK ME IF IT FELT GOOD.
HE WAS A KARATE INSTRUCTOR.
HE WOULD SEXUALLY ABUSE ME IN
THE STUDIO.
MY MOM WAS NOT THERE.
SHE WAS A NANNY.
SHE DID ODD JOBS, CLEANING
HOUSES.
WHEN SHE WAS OFF TO WORK, THAT'S
WHEN HE WOULD PREY ON ME.
MY DAD MADE ME LURE MEN TO THE
HOUSE TO HAVE SEX WITH ME SO HE
COULD WATCH.
WHEN I WAS ABOUT 15 YEARS OLD,
IT BECAME ROUTINE.
THE TIMES THAT I WOULD NOT BRING
MEN BACK, HE WOULD BEAT ME UP
AND SAY I WAS LYING, THAT I
DIDN'T TRY.
NOT ONLY WAS HE SEXUALLY ABUSING
ME, HE WAS PHYSICALLY ABUSING
ME, HITTING ME WITH BATS.
HE WOULD GRAB MY FEET AND SNACK
IT LIKE THAT.
MY KNEES WERE BRUISED AND I WAS
BED RIDDEN FOR DAYS.
I COULDN'T WALK AT ALL.
OUT OF NOWHERE, I WOULD WAKE UP
JUST BLOWS TO THE HEAD, TO THE
BODY.
HE WAS PARANOID.
MY FATHER WAS ON DRUGS THE
MAJORITY OF THE TIME THAT HE
ABUSED ME.
MY FATHER FED ME DRUGS FROM 6
YEARS OLD.
HE INTRODUCED ME TO ALCOHOL,
MARIJUANA AT THE AGE OF 8,
COCAINE AT 10.
THE ABUSE GOT WORSE WHEN HE
PULLED ME OUT OF SCHOOL.
I WASN'T ALLOWED OUTSIDE THE
HOUSE.
HE INSTALLED SURVEILLANCE
CAMERAS INSIDE THE HOUSE.
HE HAD ALARMS AS WELL AND DOGS.
WE HAD SEVEN ROTTWEILERS AT ONE
POINT.
HE HAD SENSORS UNDER THE BED.
I COULDN'T GO TO THE BATHROOM.
I HAD TO USE A BUCKET NEXT TO
THE BED.
WAKE HIM UP AND TELL HIM I HAD
TO USE THE REST ROOM.
THAT WAS RARE.
THAT WAS LIKE WAKING UP THE
BEST.
I WOULD HAVE TO COOK, CLEAN
DAILY.
BASICALLY LIVING LIKE HIS WIFE.
I NEVER TRIED TO ESCAPE.
I WISH I DID.
HE THREATENED TO KILL ME.
PLENTY OF TIME I CONTEMPLATED
HURTING HIM.
I WAS SCARED OF THE UNKNOWN.
I JUST GAVE MANY.
>> Dr. Phil: TATIANA, I'M VERY
GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
REST ASSURED, I'M NOT GOING TO
ASK YOU ANY DETAILS THAT
EMBARRASS YOU HERE.
I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT WHILE
I'M GLAD TO MEET YOU, I'M REALLY
SORRY FOR THE CIRCUMSTANCE.
MY QUESTION IN LOOKING BACK ON
THIS, HOW DO YOU THINK YOUR
FATHER WAS ABLE TO KEY THIS A
SECRET FROM THE WORLD FOR SO
MANY YEARS?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
HE'S VERY PERSONABLE, VERY
SMART, READ A LOT OF BOOKS.
>> Dr. Phil: THIS GOT TO THE
POINT THAT HE WAS PERFORMING
LIKE TEN SEX ACTS A WEEK.
THIS WAS AN INTENSE ASSAULT
PATTERN ON YOU, CORRECT?
>> THAT IS CORRECT.
>> Dr. Phil: AND IT -- THE
EARLIEST REMEMBRANCES YOU HAVE
OF THIS WERE AT WHAT AGE?
>> 6 YEARS OLD.
THE ONE PICTURE THAT I GAVE YOU
GUYS.
ME HOLDING THE DOLL.
>> Dr. Phil: RIGHT.
AND AT 6, YOU KNOW, YOU SAY THAT
HE WOULD KISS YOU, HE WOULD
TOUCH YOUR PRIVATES.
BUT IT WASN'T LONG AFTER THAT
THAT IN ADDITION TO THAT BEING
INAPPROPRIATE, WRONG AND
HUMILIATING, THINGS BEGAN TO GET
VERY PAINFUL.
CORRECT?
HE BEGAN TO VIOLATE YOUR BODY IN
THAT WAY.
WHEN WAS THAT AND WHAT HAPPENED
THEN?
>> I WAS 7 YEARS OLD.
8 YEARS OLD.
HE STARTED SEXUALLY ABUSING ME.
>> Dr. Phil: HE STARTED GIVING
YOU DRUGS.
WHAT DID YOU THINK ABOUT THAT?
DID IT SCARE YOU WHEN YOU
STARTED --
>> SCARED ME A LOT WHEN I
STARTED GETTING FUZZY.
I REMEMBER SEVERAL OCCASIONS
EXACTLY NOT KNOWING WHAT WAS
GOING TO HAPPEN AFTERWARDS.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU SAID YOU WOULD
WAKE UP SOMETIMES TO YOUR FATHER
ON TOP OF YOU.
JUST A SOMETHING THAT MAKES IT
DIFFICULT FOR ME TO USE THAT
WORD "FATHER."
THIS MAN ON TOP OF YOU, JUST
BEATING YOU.
YOU'RE ASLEEP.
YOU WAKE UP.
HE'S BEATING YOU.
WAS THERE ANY SENSE OF WHY?
>> NO.
I HAVE NO IDEA.
FOR WHATEVER REASONS, HE CAME UP
WITH HIS OWN REASONS AS TO WHY
HE WAS BEATING ME UP LIKE THAT
AND WAKING ME UP LIKE THAT.
IT WAS THROUGH HIS PARANOIA.
I KNOW THAT I HAD TO SLEEP
ALMOST WITH ONE EYE OPEN.
SCARED.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU SAID HE WOULD
TAKE A BASEBALL BAT AND BEAT THE
BOTTOMS OF YOUR FEET.
>> HE WOULD MAKE ME GIVE MY FEET
TO HIM.
I WOULD DO AS MUCH AS I WOULD.
THERE WERE TIMES THAT MY KNEES
WERE SO BRUISED, MY ELBOWS,
EVERYTHING.
HE WAS JUST SWINGING.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU SAY AT AGE 10,
HE WAS A KARATE TAE KWON DO
INSTRUCTOR.
YOU SAY HE RAPED YOU IN THE
STUDIO IN THE DRESSING ROOM.
>> CORRECT.
>> Dr. Phil: SO THERE WERE OTHER
PEOPLE AROUND, BUT HE WOULD TAKE
YOU EARLY BEFORE THE CLASS
STARTED?
>> CORRECT.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU SAY AT AGE 12
THAT HE TOOK YOU OUT OF SCHOOL.
>> HE DIDN'T WANT ME TO GET
CLOSE, OPEN UP TO SOMEBODY.
>> Dr. Phil: DO YOU FEEL GUILTY
THAT YOU SHOULD HAVE TOLD
SOMEONE?
>> I DO FEEL GUILTY.
I SHOULD HAVE NEVER LET HIM
MANIPULATE ME AND DO WHAT HE WAS
DOING TO ME.
I WAS SO SCARED AND SO
UNCERTAIN.
THAT'S ALL THAT I KNEW.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU THINK ABOUT
THIS NOW AS AN ADULT.
YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER HOW OLD YOU
WERE.
YOU CAN'T JUDGE WHAT YOU DID AT
8, 9 OR 10 WITH A 20-SOMETHING
BRAIN.
AS A CHILD, AND PEOPLE DON'T
UNDERSTAND THAT AT THAT AGE, A
PRISON IS MORE THAN MOTION
DETECTORS.
A PRISON IS MORE THAN LOCKED
DOORS.
THE PSYCHOLOGICAL PRISON, THE
PSYCHOLOGICAL BARRIERS ARE MUCH
MORE POWERFUL THAN A LOCKED
DOOR.
WHEN A CHILD IS CONTROLLED BY AN
ADULT WITH THE FEAR OF WHAT WILL
HAPPEN IF YOU TELL --
>> CORRECT.
YES.
>> Dr. Phil: AND PEOPLE WONDER
HAVING GONE THROUGH THIS HOW YOU
CAN DISCUSS IT SO CALMLY.
BUT YOU'VE LEARNED TO PUSH THIS
DOWN AND ENCAPSULATE IT, HAVEN'T
YOU?
>> I SURE HAVE, SIR.
I LIVED -- I MANAGED LIVING THAT
HORRIBLE SITUATION.
SO MY SENSE I FIGURE, YOU KNOW,
HIM OUT OF THE PICTURE IS, YOU
KNOW -- I'M OKAY.
>> Dr. Phil: AS UNIMAGINABLE AS
THIS STORY IS, YOU HAVEN'T HEARD
THE WORST OF IT YET.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Dr. Phil: DID YOU PRETEND YOU
WERE A FAMILY?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
>> TRYING TO BE NICE, BE ON HIS
GOOD SIZE.
EVEN HAVING SEX.
I WOULD LET HIM HAVE HIS WAY.
GO ON WITH IT AND GET ON ABOUT
MY DAY.
>> Announcer: MONDAY, THEIR
DAUGHTER WAS DIAGNOSED WITH
SCHIZOPHRENIA.
MOM BELIEVES THEIR SON HAS IT,
TOO.
>> HE HAS SCHIZOPHRENIA.
>> Dr. Phil: IT'S 5:00 A.M. AND
SHE'S QUESTIONING BODE ABOUT HIS
MEDS.
>> DO YOU NEED MEDICATION?
YES OR NO.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU'RE NOT
COMPETENT TO MAKE A DECISION
ABOUT WHAT MEDICATIONS HE NEEDS.
>> THEN YOU PROVIDE ME THE
DOCTOR WHO IS.
>> Announcer: THAT'S MONDAY.
THEN ON WEDNESDAY, THEY CLAIM
MOM --
>> I DRINK A LOT.
>> Announcer: IS MIA.
>> THIS IS ME TEXTING OVER AND
OVER AGAIN.
NO
Z35WDZ Z16FZ
Y35WDY Y16FY
>> THIS PICTURE, I WAS 12 YEARS
OLD.
YOU CAN TELL I WAS INTOXICATED.
ANY EYES WERE LOW.
LIKE I SMOKED SOMEONE.
HE WAS ABUSING ME WITHOUT THE
HEAVY DRUGS.
HE WAS JUST DOING IT BECAUSE HE
COULD ABUSE ME MORE.
I WOULD HATE IT WHEN HE WOULD
GET THE DRUGS.
I WOULD TELL YOU THAT MUCH.
IT WOULD BE LIKE SO MUCH LONGER
THAT I WOULD HAVE TO ENDURE IT.
MY FATHER WAS A DRUG ADDICT.
THE ABUSE WAS MORE WHEN HE WAS
ON DRUGS.
>> IT WOULD BE A WEEK OR ALL
NIGHT ABUSE.
>> Dr. Phil: FOR NEARLY 19
YEARS, TATIANA WAS HELD CAPTIVE,
FORCED TO TAKE DRUGS AND
SEXUALLY ABUSED BY HER FATHER.
THERE'S MORE TO IT THAN THAT.
>> AS A RESULT OF MY FATHER
SEXUALLY ABUSING ME, I WAS
PREGNANT FOUR TIMES WITH AN
ABORTION.
I HAVE THREE CHILDREN WITH MY
FATHER.
I WAS 16 YEARS OLD WHEN I BECAME
PREGNANT WITH MY FIRST DAUGHTER.
21 WITH MY SECOND AND 24 WITH MY
THIRD DAUGHTER.
HE WOULD MARK DOWN WITH MY
PERIOD CYCLES.
I WAS LATE.
I WAS SHOCKED.
I WAS HAPPY BUT CONFUSED AS
WELL.
WHEN I GAVE BIRTH TO MY FIRST
CHILD, IT WAS VERY SCARY.
IT WAS INTENSE.
THEY ASKED WHO THE FATHER WAS.
I SAID I DIDN'T KNOW.
THE SEXUAL ABUSE WOULD CONTINUE
THROUGH THE PREGNANCIES.
HE WOULD RAPE ME, BEAT ME.
ONE TIME WHEN I WAS PREGNANT
WITH MY YOUNGEST DAUGHTER, I WAS
SEVEN MONTHS PREGNANT.
HE TIED ME UP IN A CHAIR AND PUT
A BAG OVER MY HEAD.
I FELT LIKE I DIED AND CAME
BACK.
MY FIRST DAUGHTER WAS BORN.
I WANTED TO PROTECT HER.
SHE WAS MY LITTLE FRIEND.
I HAD NOBODY.
ALL I DID IS PLAY WITH HER.
I WAS HAPPY BUT YET I WAS REALLY
SAD.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS GOING TO
BECOME OF US.
>> Dr. Phil: SO YOU GAVE BIRTH
TO THREE OF YOUR DAD'S -- I
CAN'T SAY THAT WORD.
YOU GAVE BIRTH TO THREE -- OF
THIS MONSTER'S CHILDREN.
>> CORRECT.
>> Dr. Phil: AND YOU HAD ONE
ABORTION.
>> UH-HUH.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU'RE NOW 38.
YOU HAVE THESE CHILDREN THAT ARE
HOW OLD NOW?
>> 21, 17 AND 14.
>> Dr. Phil: 21, 17 AND 14.
AND YOU SAY THAT HAVING A CHILD
GAVE YOU PURPOSE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> Dr. Phil: GAVE YOU PURPOSE TO
EXIST, SURVIVE, GET THROUGH
THIS.
HOW DID IT CHANGE WHEN YOU HAD A
CHILD?
>> CHANGED MY WELL-BEING AS
WELL, BEING IN THE HOUSE BY
MYSELF, HAVING NOBODY ELSE TO
LEAN TO, TO, YOU KNOW, TALK TO.
IT WAS --
>> Dr. Phil: WHAT WOULD YOU DO
TO COPE?
WOULD YOU TRY TO MAKE NICE WITH
HIM?
DID YOU PRETEND YOU WERE A
FAMILY?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
>> PRETEND I WAS A FAMILY.
TRY TO BE ON HIS GOOD SIDE.
AS FAR AS HAVING SEX OR NOT, I
KNEW HE WAS GOING TO DO IT
ANYWAY.
I WOULDN'T TRY TO FIGHT HIM OFF.
I WOULD LET HIM HAVE HIS WAY SO
IT WOULD BE EASIER AND GET IT
OVER WITH.
GO ON ABOUT MY DAY.
>> Dr. Phil: AS PERVERSE AS THIS
SOUNDS AND I HAVE TO ASK THIS
BECAUSE I WANT TO GET EVERYTHING
ON THE TABLE BECAUSE I WANT TO
HELP YOU.
WERE THERE TIMES THAT YOU
CONVINCED YOURSELF THAT YOU
ENJOYED THIS IN ANY WAY?
WERE THERE TIMES WHERE YOU FOUND
PLEASURED IN A GIVEN INSTANCE
THAT YOU THOUGHT, WELL, THAT WAS
OKAY?
>> NO.
I WOULD TRY TO TELL MYSELF IT
WAS OKAY.
BUT IT NEVER FELT OKAY.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU TRIED TO TELL
YOURSELF THIS IS OKAY, IT'S LIKE
HUSBAND AND WIFE.
>> RIGHT.
BUT DEEP DOWN I KNEW IT WASN'T
OKAY.
LIKE MY EVERY DAY LIFE.
I KNOW MY PAST AND MY GIRLS ARE
NOT OKAY BUT I HAVE TO LIVE AS
IF IT'S OKAY.
>> Dr. Phil: WHO ELSE WAS AROUND
WHEN THIS WAS GOING ON?
>> JUST MY BROTHER.
HE WAS MORE IN THE HOUSE.
>> Dr. Phil: NOBODY KNEW --
>> LET ME TELL YOU THIS, SIR.
EVEN AFTER MY BROTHER, TWO YEARS
AFTER HE LEFT, HE DIDN'T COME
BACK.
>> Dr. Phil: DO YOU THINK HE
KNEW WHAT WAS GOING ON?
>> UH-HUH.
HE WAS SCARED AS WELL.
>> Dr. Phil: THE OBVIOUS
QUESTION IN EVERYBODY'S MIND IS
WHERE WAS YOUR MOTHER WHEN ALL
OF THIS WAS GOING ON?
WE'LL GET THAT ANSWER AFTER THE
BREAK.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Dr. Phil: YOU HAD THREE
CHILDREN WITH HIM.
THEY GOT TO THE AGE WHERE HE
STARTED ABUSING YOU.
>> CORRECT.
>> Dr. Phil: DID HE HURT THEM?
>> Announcer: THIS FEBRUARY,
THEIR DAUGHTER IS SCHIZOPHRENIC.
NOW MOM SAYS HER SON IS, TOO.
>> HE HAS AUTISM AND CHILDHOOD
SCHIZOPHRENIA.
>> Announcer: A SHOW --
>> Dr. Phil: IT'S 5:00 A.M. AND
SHE'S QUESTIONING BODE ABOUT HIS
MEDS.
>> DO YOU NEED MEDICATION?
YES OR NO.
>> Announcer: THAT'S NEVER --
>> Dr. Phil: YOU'RE NOT
COMPETENT TO MAKE A DECISION
ABOUT HIS MEDICATIONS.
>> THEN YOU PROVIDE ME THE
DOCTOR THAT IS.
>> Dr. Phil: TO BE ASKING THAT
QUESTION IS RECKLESS AND
IRRESPONSIBLE.
>> Announcer: ENDED LIKE THIS.
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>> THIS IS OUR HOUSE.
THIS IS WHERE I LIVED.
IF THE WALLS COULD TALK, THEY
WOULD SAY A LOT.
ONE DAY MY FATHER JUST STABBED
ME SO HARD IN MY HAND THAT IT
ALMOST WENT ALL THE WAY THROUGH.
I STILL HAVE NERVE DAMAGE ON
THAT HAND TILL THIS DAY.
HE WOULD TASE ME AS WELL.
I WAS AROUND 14, 15.
HE DID IT LIKE FIVE TIMES.
HE WAS TAUNTING ME, I'M GOING TO
DO IT, I WAS GOING TO DO IT.
I WAS REALLY SCARED.
>> Dr. Phil: TATIANA SAYS IN
ORDER TO COPE WITH HER FATHER'S
CONSTANT A BECAUSE, SHE TRADE TO
CONVINCE HERSELF THAT THEY WERE
IN LOVE, THIS WAS NORMAL, THERE
WAS SOME WAY TO JUST LIVE WITH
THIS AS THOUGH IT WAS OKAY.
KNOWING DEEP DOWN INSIDE IT
WASN'T OH SAY, BUT SHE WOULD TRY
IN HER MIND TO ACCOMMODATE, TO
ADAPT TO IT IN SOME WAY.
WHERE WAS YOUR MOTHER WHEN THIS
WAS GOING ON?
>> MY MOM WORKED A LOT.
SHE STILL DOES.
SHE'S A WORKER.
I MEAN, SHE WAS GONE MOST OF THE
TIME.
>> Dr. Phil: AND WHAT WAS HER
JOB?
>> SHE USED TO HOUSE SIT, DOG
SIT.
IN THE BEGINNING, SHE WAS DOING
ODD JOBS.
THEN SHE WAS A CAREGIVER.
SHE TURNED HER PROFESSION TO
BEING A CAREGIVER AND SHE WAS
GONE.
>> Dr. Phil: SO SHE WOULD TAKE
CARE OF THOSE THAT WERE BED
RIDDEN AND SHE WOULD BE GONE
SOMETIMES 24/7 DAYS AT A TIME,
RIGHT?
>> 24/7, YEAH.
>> Dr. Phil: DID SHE HAVE NO
IDEA THIS WAS GOING ON?
>> NO, SIR.
EVERYBODY ASKED ME, YOU KNOW,
EVEN IF SHE WERE TO HAVE ASKED
ME, I WOULD HAVE SAID NO.
THAT'S NOT GOING ON.
MY MOM WAS ABUSED BY HIM AS
WELL.
YOU KNOW, SHE -- I DON'T KNOW,
SIR.
I GET WHAT EVERYBODY SAYS, SHE
SHOULD HAVE SEEN SOMETHING.
IT'S HARD WHEN YOU'RE IN THIS
SITUATION YOURSELF.
>> Dr. Phil: NO, I GET IT.
HE ABUSED HER.
>> CORRECT.
>> Dr. Phil: HE ABUSED YOU.
YOU HAD THREE CHILDREN WITH HIM.
>> UH-HUH.
>> Dr. Phil: SO THEY GROW UP IN
THIS HOUSE.
THEY GOT TO AN AGE, THEY GOT TO
THE AGE WHERE HE STARTED ABUSING
YOU.
>> CORRECT.
>> Dr. Phil: DID HE HURT THEM?
>> HE DID HURT THEM PHYSICALLY
ONE TIME.
I REMEMBER SEVERAL TIMES JUST,
YOU KNOW, KIND OF SPANKING AND
STUFF LIKE THAT.
>> Dr. Phil: DO YOU KNOW IF HE
EVER SEXUALLY ASSAULTED ANY OF
THE THREE.
>> I'VE HEARD FROM MY DAUGHTER
THAT HE TRIED TO SEXUALLY
ASSAULT HER WHEN SHE WAS 7 YEARS
OLD.
>> Dr. Phil: WHAT DID YOU THINK
WHEN SHE TOLD YOU THAT?
>> I WAS EVEN MORE DISGUSTED BY
HIM.
>> Dr. Phil: WHAT DID YOU SAY TO
HER?
>> I TOLD HER THAT I WAS SORRY,
THAT I DID NOT REMEMBER.
IT WAS ONE INCIDENT THAT SHE
SAID THAT I GOT HIM IN THE ROOM
WITH HER, BUT I WAS -- I HAD
BLACKED OUT.
I DIDN'T KNOW THIS HAD HAPPENED
UNTIL YEARS LATER AND THAT I
ATTACKED HIM.
>> Dr. Phil: SO ALCOHOL, DRUGS
TO CONTROL YOU.
>> UH-HUH.
>> Dr. Phil: THIS INCLUDED
CRACK, METH.
>> UH-HUH.
>> Dr. Phil: HE WOULD DO
ANYTHING HE COULD TO ALTER YOUR
CONSCIOUSNESS, RIGHT?
>> THAT'S CORRECT.
>> Dr. Phil: AND KEEP YOU IN THE
ZONE.
LOOKING BACK, HOW YOUNG WERE YOU
WHEN HE FIRST GAVE YOU CRACK?
>> ABOUT 14 YEARS OLD.
>> Dr. Phil: METH.
>> SAME, 14.
>> Dr. Phil: YEAH.
HOW DO YOU FEEL SEEING THAT?
>> I HAVE NEVER SEEN THAT
FOOTAGE BEFORE.
>> Dr. Phil: IS IT GOOD TO SEE
HIM SHACKLE
Smooth, easy strokes.
When you're raising a child...
Pinch.
be soft.
Ah.
When you're doing
it alone, be strong.
Thanks, dad.
Life takes softness and
strength, which is why
we make Angel Soft
with a balance of both.
Our grandparents checked
their smartphones
zero times a day.
Times change.
Eyes haven't.
That's why there's Ocuvite.
Screen light...
Sunlight...
Longer hours...
Eyes today are stressed.
But Ocuvite has vital
nutrients...
...to help protect them.
Ocuvite.
Eye nutrition for today.
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>> Dr. Phil: TATIANA FINALLY
ESCAPED HER 19 YEARS OF ABUSE
AFTER HER FATHER WAS ARRESTED,
BUT SHE NEARLY DIED IN THE
PROCESS.
>> ONE DAY MY FATHER WAS
EXTREMELY HIGH ON
METHAMPHETAMINE AFTER DAYS OF
NOT EATING AND SLEEPING.
HE THOUGHT I WAS TRYING TO KILL
HIM.
HE BECAME PARANOID.
I SAID IF YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
GOING TO DIE, LET'S GO TO THE
HOSPITAL.
HE HAD A KNIFE.
HE STARTED DRIVING ME TO THE
HOSPITAL.
WE GOT TO THE HOSPITAL AND HE
CIRCLED AROUND SEVERAL TIMES.
I WAS TELLING HIM, THE KIDS ARE
THERE BY THEMSELVES.
FIVE ROTTWEILERS IN A HOTEL
ROOM.
I TRIED TO JUMP OUT.
I WASN'T FAST ENOUGH.
HE STABBED ME TWICE IN THE
CHEST.
I DON'T REMEMBER LOOKING BACK.
HE RAN.
HE CAME OUT AFTER ME.
I WENT IN FOR SURGERY.
THE KNIFE WOUND WAS SO DEEP, IT
WAS A SENT METER FROM THE SACK
OF MY HEART.
I TOLD THEM MY BOYFRIEND DID
THIS.
WHEN I WOKE UP FROM MY SURGERY,
I TOLD THE AUTHORITIES THE
CHILDREN ARE MY FATHER'S
CHILDREN.
I DON'T WANT TO GO BACK TO HIM.
WHEN THEY SAID HE WAS IN
CUSTODY, YOU CAN ONLY IMAGINE
THE RELIEF THAT I GOT FROM THAT
NEWS.
SOMETHING THAT I THOUGHT I WOULD
NEVER EXPERIENCE.
IT WAS A REBIRTH.
I CALL THAT MY BORN AGAIN DAY.
NOT ONLY I ALMOST DIED, I WAS
FREE.
>> Dr. Phil: HOW DO YOU FEEL
SEEING THAT?
>> I HAVE NEVER SEEN THAT
FOOTAGE BEFORE.
I'M IN SHOCK RIGHT NOW.
WOW.
>> Dr. Phil: WHAT DO YOU THINK
AS YOU LOOK AT THAT?
>> I AM JUST -- I HAVE NO WORDS
FOR IT RIGHT NOW.
THAT'S --
>> Dr. Phil: SO IT GOOD TO SEE
HIM SHACKLED?
>> IT'S GOOD TO SEE HIM
SHACKLED.
VERY GOOD TO SEE HIM SHACKLED.
BUT ALSO -- IT'S SAD.
HOW CAN A FATHER DO THIS TO
SOMEBODY?
LIKE I STILL -- I JUST WISH
EVERY DAY THAT HE DIDN'T HAVE TO
DO THAT.
YOU KNOW?
THAT HE COULD JUST BE YOUR DAD.
I MISSED OUT ON IT.
MY GIRLS MISSED OUT ON IT.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU FEEL CHEATED
OUT OF WHAT YOU DIDN'T HAVE AS
WELL AS WHAT DID HAPPEN TO YOU.
>> EXACTLY.
EVERYTHING.
MY WHOLE LIFE I FEEL HAS BEEN A
CHEAT.
IF IT WASN'T FOR MY CHILDREN, I
WOULDN'T BE HERE RIGHT NOW,
DR. PHIL.
I WOULDN'T.
I WOULD HAVE ENDED MY LIFE A
LONG TIME AGO.
>> Dr. Phil: ARE YOU GLAD THAT
YOU HAVE SURVIVED?
>> I AM SUPER GLAD THAT I
SURVIVED, YES.
I KNOW I HAVE A WHOLE LOT MORE
SURVIVING TO DO.
>> Dr. Phil: WHAT IF I TOLD YOU
THAT SOME THINGS WERE GOING TO
HAPPEN TODAY THAT WERE GOING TO
CHANGE YOUR LIFE?
>> I THINK GOOD THINGS OR BAD
THINGS.
SORRY.
>> Dr. Phil: I WOULD EXPECT YOU
TO CHECK ALL OF THE BOXES OFF,
ALL THE POSSIBILITIES.
GIVEN WHO YOU ARE.
GOOD THINGS.
>> GOOD.
I WOULD BE SUPER HAPPY.
>> Dr. Phil: TATIANA'S FATHER
CHOSE TO REPRESENT HIMSELF IN
COURT.
TO THIS DAY, HE NEVER ADMITTED
HE DID ANYTHING WRONG.
SO WHERE DO YOU GO FROM HERE?
WHAT DOES SHE DO?
HE'S IN PRISON, SHE'S NOT.
IS SHE FREE?
OR IS HE STILL CONTROLLING HER?
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT WHEN WE
COME BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
>> I WOULD DESCRIBE HIM AS AN
EVIL SOCIOPATH NARCISSIST.
JUST HAD TO BE THE MOST EXTREME
CASE OF SEXUAL ABUSE I HAVE EVER
INVESTIGATED.
TALKING WITH HIM WAS LIKE
LOOKING AT THE DEVIL.
THE HAIR ON THE BACK OF MY NECK
STOOD UP.
>> Announcer: MONDAY ON AN
ALL-NEW "DR. PHIL."
SHE BELIEVED HER SON IS
SCHIZOPHRENIC.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU'RE NOT
COMPETENT TO MAKE DECISIONS ON
(MEG VO)
I can just suck up my
endometriosis pain...
Or I can...
(DIANE VO)
I can keep apologizing...
Or I can...
(SHERRY VO)
I can hope my pain gets better
on its own...
Or I can talk to
my gynecologist today!
(AVO)
You didn't choose to have
endometriosis...
but you can choose to ask
if ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA is specifically
developed for women
with moderate to severe
endometriosis pain.
In clinical trials,
ORILISSA was proven to reduce 3
common types of
endometriosis pain,
painful periods,
pelvic pain in between
periods,
and pain with sex.
Don't use ORILISSA if you are or
may be pregnant,
have osteoporosis,
severe liver disease, or are
taking drugs like
cyclosporine or gemfibrozil.
It may cause abnormal
liver tests.
ORILISSA may change your
periods, making it hard
to know if you are pregnant.
It does not prevent pregnancy.
Use birth control that does not
contain hormones.
ORILISSA may cause suicidal
thoughts or actions.
It may also cause bone loss.
Ask your gynecologist if
ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA. Made for endo pain.
Z35K8Z Z16FZ
Y35K8Y Y16FY
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>> AT MY DAD'S TRIAL, I
TESTIFIED.
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
I HATED IT.
I HAD NOT SPOKEN WITH HIM SINCE
HE STABBED ME.
DURING THE TRIAL, HAVING TO HEAR
HIS VOICE, IT WAS NERVE RACKING
AND TO TOP IT OFF, HE WAS
REPRESENTING HIMSELF AND IT WAS
LIKE HE WAS HAVING A
CONVERSATION WITH ME.
IT WAS REALLY DISGUSTING.
I REMEMBER THAT HE ASKED.
SO YOU'RE GOING TO TELL ME YOU
DIDN'T HAVE A GOOD CHILDHOOD?
A GOOD UPBRINGING?
THAT PISSED ME OFF.
HE SAID YOU HAD THE OPPORTUNITY
TO SPEAK OUT ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED.
YOU NEVER DID.
>> Dr. Phil: IN A UNANIMOUS
DECISION, UNANIMOUS DECISION, A
JURY FOUND TATIANA'S FATHER,
LINDOLFO, GUILTY OF FORCIBLE
RAPE, SODOMY AND INFLICTING
GREAT HARM ON TATIANA.
[APPLAUSE]
THE KEY EVIDENCE, DNA TESTS
CONFIRMED THAT HE WAS BIOLOGICAL
SPERM DONOR OF TATIANA'S
CHILDREN.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> LINDOLFO IS THE MOST PURE
EVIL MAN I HAVE EVER MET IN MY
LIFE.
I WOULD DESCRIBE LINDOLFO AS AN
EVIL SOCIOPAST NARCISSIST.
I WAS THE LEAD DETECTIVE ON THE
SEXUAL ASSAULT CASE INVOLVING
TATIANA.
I'VE INVESTED OVER 3,000 SEXUAL
ASSAULT CASES.
THIS HAD TO BE THE MOST EXTREME
CASE THAT I'VE EVER
INVESTIGATED.
AFTER TAKING THE INITIAL REPORT,
COLLECTED DNA EVIDENCE FROM HER
AND THE THREE CHILDREN, TO GET
THE SAMPLE FROM LINDOLFO, WHO IS
STILL IN CUSTODY FROM THE
ATTEMPT MURDER.
THE ENTIRE TIME I WAS OBTAINING
HIS DNA SAMPLE, HE ADAMANTLY
DENIED ABUSING HER SEXUALLY,
WITH NARCOTICS OR ALCOHOL.
THE DNA WAS CLEAR EVIDENCE THAT
HE WAS IN FACT THE FATHER.
IN 2009 DURING THE TRIAL,
LINDOLFO DECIDED TO REPRESENT
HIMSELF.
DURING THE CROSS EXAMINATION
WHEN TATIANA WAS ON THE STAND,
LINDOLFO ACCUSED HER SEVERAL
TIMES OF ACTUALLY WANTING TO
ENGAGE IN SEX AND MAKING IT UP
TO RUIN HIS LIFE.
TALKING WITH LINDOLFO WAS LIKE
LOOKING AT THE DEVIL.
HE LOOKED RIGHT THROUGH ME.
RAGE AND HATRED COMING FROM HIS
EYES.
THE HAIR ON THE BACK OF MY NECK
STOOD UP.
AS LINDOLFO TOLD ME THAT HE WAS
GOING TO KILL ME AND KILL HER AS
SOON AS HE GOT OUT BECAUSE WE
RUINED HIS LIFE.
ABSOLUTELY ONE OF THE MOST
HEINOUS INDIVIDUALS THAT I'VE
EVER HAD TO DEAL WITH.
>> Dr. Phil: JOINING US NOW IS
RICK CARR.
RICK WAS THE LEAD INVESTIGATOR
ON TATIANA'S CASE.
THANKS SO MUCH FOR BEING HERE.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Dr. Phil: YOU SPENT THE TIME
INVESTIGATING THIS, QUESTIONING
HIM.
IT SENT CHILLS DOWN YOUR SPINE.
YOU'RE PROBABLY THE ONLY OTHER
PERSON ON THE PLANET THAT CAN
IMAGINE WHAT SHE WENT THROUGH
BECAUSE YOU DEALT WITH THIS GUY.
IT HAD TO JUST BE HORRIFIC.
>> IT WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
THE ONE THING THAT ALWAYS STUCK
OUT IN MY MIND, IS HOW
COURAGEOUS SHE WAS FROM THE
FIRST MOMENT I MET HER TILL THE
SENTENCING.
SHE WAS UNBELIEVABLY BRAVE.
JUST AS SHE'S BEING HERE TODAY
AND I -- 30 YEARS OF POLICE
WORK, THE MOST COURAGEOUS VICTIM
I HAVE EVER MET.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Dr. Phil: I AGREE WITH THAT.
THIS GUY WAS INCREDIBLY
NARCISSISTIC.
RIGHT UP TO THE DNA, HE DENIED
ANY INVOLVEMENT DOING ANYTHING
AT ALL, RIGHT?
>> ENTIRELY, YES.
>> IT WAS IT WAS PROVEN THROUGH
DNA EVIDENCE THAT HE IN FACT HAD
MOLESTED HER, ASSAULTED HER,
RAPED HER, THEN HE STARTED TO
JUST BLAME HER.
SHE WANTED THIS.
>> SHE WANTED IT.
SHE BECAME  LY -- BASICALLY
SEXUALLY ASSAULTED HIM.
>> Dr. Phil: HE TURNED DOWN A
PLEA DEAL.
>> I BELIEVE THE INITIAL OFFER
WAS A 30-YEAR SENTENCE WHICH HE
TURNED DOWN.
>> Dr. Phil: WHY DO YOU THINK HE
TURNED IT DOWN?
>> TO BEING THE ULTIMATE
NARCISSIST.
NOW WE CAN MAKE ANOTHER SHOW
ABOUT HIM WHERE HE GETS TO ABUSE
HER EVEN MORE DURING THE
TESTIMONY.
>> Dr. Phil: HE TRADED 79 YEARS
IN PRISON TO HARASS YOU ONE MORE
TIME.
>> I KNOW.
I DID NOT KNOW THIS.
THIS IS THE FIRST THAT I HEAR.
I NEVER KNEW THIS.
>> Dr. Phil: HE HAD A DEAL FOR
30 YEARS.
INSTEAD, HE GOT 109 JUST SO HE
COULD HARASS YOU ONE MORE TIME.
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW MUCH WE
APPRECIATE YOU BEING HERE TODAY
AND YOUR SPONSORSHIP OF HER AND
YOUR COMMITMENT TO THIS CASE.
>> MY PLEASURE.
THANK YOU, DR. PHIL.
>> Dr. Phil: THAT'S WHY I BLEED
BLUE.
NEXT, TATIANA SAYS TWO OF HER
THREE CHILDREN KNOW THAT HER
FATHER IS THEIR FATHER.
SHE REALLY WANTS TO KNOW HOW TO
TELL THE YOUNGEST, IF SHE
SHOULD.
SHE SAYS WHAT DO I DO ABOUT
THAT?
I'M GOING TO ANSWER THAT
QUESTION AFTER THE
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
A great dishwasher needs a great
detergent.
So GE Appliances tested Finish
on over 5000 dishes
proving dish after sparking dish
that it's not just clean,
it's Finished.
Switch to Finish Quantum.
Recommended by GE Appliances.
KFC's got four ways
to feed a family
for just 20 bucks
it's deli...
Son of a biscuit.
Well, that worked out.
Bring home dinner with any of
KFC's 20 dollar fill ups.
My name is
Elaine Barber,
and I'm a
five-year cancer survivor.
Surviving for five years
is a big deal.
I had so many people at CTCA
helping me find a way to go
through the treatments.
The reality of cancer is
not everybody survives.
At CTCA,
they have a huge
celebrate life event.
That was amazing
because the whole day
was about all of the survivors.
I'm excited about my future.
Learn more at
cancercenter.com/Philadelphia.
>> Dr. Phil: HEY, WE'RE TAPING
SEASON 17 OF "DR. PHIL."
IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE IN THE
LOS ANGELES AREA AND WANT TO
WATCH A LIVE TAPING, VISIT
drphil.com AND CLICK "BE IN THE
AUDIENCE."
TICKETS ARE FREE AND I HOPE TO
SEE YOU SOON!
COME ON, I'M ALL BY MYSELF!
>> IN THE PAST, I DATED MEN THAT
HIT ME, PUSHED ME, VERBALLY
ABUSED ME.
I TAKE SO MUCH ABUSE FROM OTHER
MEN BECAUSE IN MY MIND, NO ABUSE
WILL EVER AMOUNT TO THE ABUSE
THAT I'VE ALREADY BEEN THROUGH.
BY SOMEBODY TREATING ME WRONG OR
EVEN HITTING ME, IT'S NOT GOING
TO COMPARE.
I EVEN TOLD MY CURRENT
SIGNIFICANT OTHER RIGHT NOW, THE
ONLY WAY YOU COULD EVER REALLY
HURT ME WOULD BE IS IF YOU CUT A
LIMB OR YOU KILL ME I BECAUSE MY
FATHER HAS DONE IT ALL.
>> Dr. Phil: AFTER BEING HELD
PRISONER AND PHYSICALLY AND
SEXUALLY ABUSED FOR 19 YEARS,
EVERY DAY, BY HER FATHER,
TATIANA SAYS IT'S STILL A
STRUGGLE.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT TWO THINGS.
>> UH-HUH.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU'RE YOUNGEST
DOESN'T
RIGHT?
>> CORRECT.
>> Dr. Phil: THE QUESTION
BECOMES DO YOU WANT HER TO FIND
OUT FROM YOU OR FROM THE
INTERNET.
>> ME.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU DEFINITELY WANT
HER IN A CONTROLLED AND LOVING
ENVIRONMENT WHEN YOU TELL HER
THIS.
>> CORRECT.
>> Dr. Phil: AND WHEN YOU DO
TELL HER, YOU WANT TO BE SURE
THAT YOU'RE PREPARED TO BUST
SOME MYTHS.
WE'LL HELP YOU WITH TALKING
POINTS HERE THAT YOU CAN USE
WHEN YOU TALK TO HER.
YOU WANT TO BUST SOME MYTHS.
PEOPLE THINK IF THERE'S AN
INCESTUOUS RELATIONSHIP, THERE'S
PROBLEMS WITH INTELLECTUAL
DEVELOPMENT AND HEALTH ISSUES.
THERE IS A HIGHER RISK FOR
CERTAIN COMPLICATIONS.
BUT THAT IS NOT A GIVEN.
AS YOU HAVE SEEN WITH YOUR OTHER
DAUGHTERS.
YOU HAVE WONDERFUL DAUGHTERS AND
THEY'RE RIGHT AND THRIVING.
ALL OF THAT.
SO YOU NEED TO DISPEL SOME MYTHS
SO SHE DOESN'T HAVE A
MISUNDERSTANDING OF WHAT SHE'S
IN FOR.
YOU'RE GOING TO WANT TO TELL HER
THAT IN EVERY DARK CLOUD,
THERE'S A SILVER LINING.
AND FOR YOU SHE IS THAT SILVER
LINING.
THERE'S CERTAINLY NOTHING FOR
HER TO BE ASHAMED OF.
THERE'S NOTHING FOR YOU TO BE A
SHAMED OF.
YOU TWO WERE VICTIMIZED IN THIS.
BUT THERE ARE SOME TALKING
POINTS THAT YOU CAN HAVE WHEN
YOU TALK TO HER.
I THINK YOU SHOULD DO THAT IN A
WAY THAT IS SURROUNDED BY LOVE
AND IF THE OTHER TWO SISTERS
COULD BE THERE AND YOU GUYS CAN
JUST DO THIS IN A MATTER OF
UNITY WHERE SHE HAS AN
OPPORTUNITY TO WRAP HER HEAD
AROUND IT, WE'LL GIVE YOU SOME
TALKING POINTS IN DETAIL ABOUT
HOW BEST TO DO THAT.
BUT SHE'S OLD ENOUGH TO DO IT.
THIS IS THE TIME TO DO IT.
THE TIME TO DO WAS NOT WHEN SHE
WAS 7 OR 8 AND IT'S NOT FIVE
YEARS FROM NOW.
THE TIME IS NOW.
WE'LL HELP YOU DO THAT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU KNOW, I ASKED AT THAT
TIME A FEW MINUTES AGO, I SAID,
WHAT IF TODAY IS A DAY THAT CAN
REALLY CHANGE HER LIFE FOR THE
BETTER?
SHE CALLED ME ON THAT.
I DO HAVE A PLAN.
I'M GOING TO TELL HER WHAT IT IS
WHEN WE COME BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
Abdominal Pain?
Discomfort?
You may be the one in
six living with IBS.
Ask your doctor about
nonprescription
IBgard for the daily
dietary management of IBS.
IBgard - Daily
Gut Health Gard.
I've always been amazed
by what's next.
And still going for my best,
even though I live with
a higher risk of stroke
due to Afib not caused by
a heart valve problem.
So if there's a better treatment
than warfarin...
I want that too.
ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS is proven
to reduce stroke risk
better than warfarin.
Plus has significantly less
major bleeding than warfarin.
ELIQUIS is FDA-approved
and has both.
What's next?
Reeling in a nice one.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS
unless your doctor tells you to,
as stopping increases your risk
of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS If you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily
and it may take longer than
usual for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden sign of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase your
bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor
about all planned medical
or dental procedures.
ELIQUIS, the number one
cardiologist-prescribed
blood thinner.
Ask your doctor if ELIQUIS
is what's next for you.
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>> DR. PHIL: WANT TO KNOW WHAT
IS COMING UP ON DR. PHIL, VISIT
OUR WEBSITE AND SUBSCRIBE TO OUR
E-MAIL NEWSLETTER.
YOU'LL GET WEEKLY UPDATES, LIFE
STRATEGIES AND EXCLUSIVE VIDEO
YOU WON'T FIND ANYWHERE ELSE.
>> PLUS ON DRPHIL.COM, YOU CAN
SEE SNEAK PREVIEWS OF UPCOMING
SHOWS.
LOG ON TODAY!
>> Dr. Phil: TATIANA, I SAID,
ARE YOU REALLY FREE OF HIM?
YOU REALLY AREN'T.
>> HUH-UH.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU'RE NOT.
BECAUSE YOU HAVE IN A SENSE
STILL GIVEN SOME OF YOUR POWER
AWAY.
AND HE IS ABLE FOR YOU TO FEEL
IN ANY WAY LIKE YOU'RE DAMAGED
GOODS.
LIKE YOU'RE SECOND CLASS.
THAT MEANS THAT YOU HAVE A
DAMAGED PERSONAL TRUTH.
AND THE PROBLEM WITH THAT IS, WE
GENERATE THE RESULTS AND LIFE
THAT WE THINK WE DESERVE.
I SEE OPEN WOUNDS IN YOU THAT
ARE NOT HEALED YET.
PEOPLE ASK ME SOMETIMES WHERE I
LEARN THINGS THAT I LEARN AND
GET COUNSEL.
I READ A BOOK ONE TIME THAT IS
THE MOST POWERFUL BOOK I HAVE
EVER READ.
IT'S "MAN'S SEARCH FOR MEANING"
BY VICTOR FRANKLE.
HE'S A JEWISH PSYCHIATRIST THAT
IS A PRISONER OF WAR.
HE WROTE ABOUT THE EXPERIENCES.
HE SAID THEY CONTROLLED WHEN I
LIVED OR DIED EVERY DAY.
THEY CONTROLLED WHETHER I SAT OR
STOOD, WHETHER I ATE OR STARVED.
THEY CONTROLLED EVERY ASPECT OF
MY LIFE BUT ONE.
THEY COULDN'T CONTROL THE
ATTITUDE I TOOK ABOUT IT.
>> UH-HUH.
>> Dr. Phil: THEY COULDN'T
CONTROL MY SPIRIT, THEY COULDN'T
CONTROL MY MIND.
AND WHAT ATTITUDE I TALK ABOUT
IT WAS, I'M GOING TO SURVIVE
BECAUSE I MUST CREATE MEANING TO
THIS SUFFERING.
AND THAT'S WHY THE TITLE OF THE
BOOK IS "MAN'S SEARCH FOR
MEANING."
YOUR JOB IS TO FIND THE MEANING,
WHY DID THIS HAPPEN TO YOU, HOW
CAN YOU USE THIS IN THE WORLD.
YOU'RE USING YOUR LIFE RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE THERE ARE WOMEN RIGHT
NOW THAT ARE TRAPPED IN
SITUATIONS PROBABLY NOT AS
EGREGIOUS AS YOURS BUT TRAPPED
IN SITUATIONS THAT SAY I DO NEED
TO REACH OUT, I DO NEED TO TELL
SOMEONE.
YOU'RE SAVING THOUSANDS OF
WOMEN'S LIVES AS YOU SIT THERE
IN THIS CHAIR RIGHT NOW.
>> I HOPE SO.
I SURE HOPE SO, DR. PHIL.
I DO.
[APPLAUSE]
>> BUT YOU CANNOT GIVE AWAY WHAT
YOU DON'T HAVE.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF
YOURSELF FIRST.
I WANT TO INTRODUCE YOU TO
SOMEBODY ON POLYCOM.
A DEAR, DEAR FRIEND OF MINE.
HIS NAME IS MILES ADCOX.
HE'S THE OWNER AND CEO OF AN
ORGANIZATION CALLED ONSITE.
ONSITE IS A PLACE THAT DOES
INTENSIVE WORKSHOPS FOR PEOPLE
THAT HAVE BEEN THROUGH TRAUMA TO
HELP THEM WITH SELF-WORTH AND
SELF-ESTEEM AND MENTAL HEALTH
ISSUES.
IT'S THE MOST BEAUTIFUL CAMPUS
YOU'VE EVER SEEN IN YOUR LIFE.
THE ONLY PROBLEM WITH IT IS
PEOPLE DON'T WANT TO LEAVE ONCE
THEY GET THERE.
MILES HAVE THE CREATOR AND RUNS
THIS ORGANIZATION.
MILES, HOW ARE YOU DOING TODAY?
>> DOING WELL.
HONORED TO BE HERE.
>> Dr. Phil: THANK YOU FOR
JOINING US.
YOU'VE BEEN LISTENING TO OUR
CONVERSATION THE WHOLE WAY.
CAN YOU HELP WITH US THIS
PRECIOUS WOMAN?
>> NOT ONLY CAN I, TATIANA, I'M
HONORED TO.
HONESTLY.
I'M FORTUNATE, I GET TO
REPRESENT SOME OF THE BRIGHTEST
TRAUMA PRACTITIONERS IN THE
COUNTRY IN MY PLACE.
NEED TO TELL YOU, THEY'RE
SOPHISTICATED CLINICIANS BUT
THEY'RE HUMAN, FIRST.
WE OBSESS ABOUT CREATING
EMOTIONAL SAFETY AND
PSYCHOLOGICAL SAFETY HERE.
I DON'T KNOW THAT I EVER MET A
HUMAN MORE DESERVING OF HAVING
THAT HEALING MAYBE FOR THE FIRST
TIME, TO BE SEEN, TO BE HEARD,
TO BE VALUED, LOVED AND
RESPECTED AND UNPACK A LOT OF
THAT BACK  -- BAGGAGE THAT
YOU'VE BEEN CARRYING.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Dr. Phil: WE'RE OFFERING THIS
TO YOU AND I WANT YOU TO TAKE
THAT HELP.
WILL YOU TAKE THAT HELP?
>>LY DEFINITELY DO SO.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Dr. Phil: ALL RIGHT.
NOW --
[APPLAUSE]
I ALSO WANT TO ADD MY DEAR
FRIEND THAT WILL WORK WITH
ONSITE.
WHEN YOU GET OUT OF THERE, THIS
IS COACH MIKE BAYER HERE.
COACH MIKE BAYER IS A LIFE
COACH.
HE'S REALLY EXPERIENCED AND
LOVED BY HIS CLIENTS.
HE WORKS WITH A LIST
CELEBRITIES, EVERYDAY PEOPLE AND
HE FOCUSES ON HELPING CLIENTS
BRING PATTERNS IN THEIR LIVES
AND IN A REAL ACTION-ORIENTED
WAY.
WHAT WE WANT TO DO IS GET YOU A
LIFE COACH THAT IS
ELBOW-TO-ELBOW,
SHOULDER-TO-SHOULDER WITH YOU TO
SAY I'M GOING TO CHANGE MY WALK
IN THIS WORLD.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE DIFFERENCE
CHOICES, MAYBE IT'S DIFFERENT
CAREER, WHATEVER IT IS.
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE A
PERSONAL LIFE COACH THAT WALKS
YOU EVERY STEP OF THE WAY AND
STARTS PUTTING YOUR LIFE
TOGETHER THE WAY YOU DESERVE FOR
IT TO BE.
MIKE, TELL HER WHAT WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT HERE.
>> YOU DESERVE TO HAVE THE
BIGGEST, BEST LIFE POSSIBLE.
SO WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO, WE'RE
GOING TO LOOK AT ALL THE THINGS
THAT YOU WERE LACKING.
EDUCATION, PARENTING CLASSES SO
YOU DON'T RECREATE ANYTHING
AMONGST YOUR KIDS.
INTIMACY COURSES.
WE'LL DEVELOP AND DEVISE A PLAN
SO YOU GET THE LIFE THAT YOU
DESERVE.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> Dr. Phil: MIKE IS -- HE'S NOT
A LIFE COACH, HE'S THE LIFE
COACH.
HE HAS A NEW BOOK CALLED "BEST
A LIFE COACH, HE IS THE LIFE
COACH.
HE HAS A NEW BOOK CALLED BEST
SELF, BEAT YOU, ONLY BETTER,
AND THAT BOOK WAS WRITTEN FOR
YOU.
FAIR ENOUGH?
>> FAIR ENOUGH.
>> OKAY, WE HAVE A DEAL.
>> [ APPLAUSE ]>> I WANT TO
THANK ALL OF MY GUEST TODAY.
A VERY SPECIAL THANKS TO RICK
CARR, AND COACH MIKE BAER, AND
MILES, THANK YOU FOR CHANGING
YOUR SCHEDULE, AND JOINING US
TODAY.
FROM ON-SITE.
ALL THE REST OF YOU, WE WILL
SEE YOU NEXT TIME, THANKS SO
MUCH.
>> [ APPLAUSE ]
>>> WE BEGIN RIGHT NOW AND
FIVE, WITH TWO BREAKING STORIES.
TWO WOMEN, WHO HAVE ACCUSED
VIRGINIA LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR
JUSTIN FAIRFAX ARE GOING TO
TESTIFY BEFORE STATE LAWMAKERS.
REPUBLICANS ARE PLANNING PUBLIC
HEARINGS INTO THE ALLEGED SEX
ASSAULT ALLEGATIONS, DESPITE
DEMOCRATIC ALLEGATIONS -- THAT
IT WILL TURN INTO A BIPARTISAN
SHOW.
REPUBLICAN DELICATE MADE THE
STATEMENT ON HOW TO DO, AND HE
SAID FAIRFAX WHO HAS DENIED THE
ALLEGATIONS, HAS BEEN INVITED
TO TESTIFY AS WELL, THE DATE
HAS NOT YET BEEN SET.
FOR THE HEARING.
>>> SO, HOW HARD IS IT TO
PROSECUTE A WELL-KNOWN PERSON
FOR SEX CRIMES?
COMING UP A LITTLE BIT LATER,
WE'RE GOING TO HEAR FROM A
COUNTY PROSECUTOR WHO IS GOING
TO BREAK IT DOWN FOR US.
>>> NEW DEVELOPMENT TONIGHT,
AND THAT TERRIFYING BROOMSTICK
ATTACK ON 14th, AND THE
FOOTBALL LOCKER ROOM AT
DAMASCUS HIGH SCHOOL.
A MONTGOMERY COUNTY JUDGE HAS
JUST ORDERED THE SECOND OF THE
FOUR YOUNG DEFENDANTS
TRANSFERRED BACK FROM ADULT
COURT COME TO JUVENILE COURT.
WE ARE THERE.
>>REPORTER: 26, TWO TO GO, THE
PROSECUTOR SAYS AT THIS POINT,
HE IS NOT SURE WHETHER HE WILL
ARGUE THAT THE OTHER
DEFENDANTS, THE TEENAGE
DEFENDANTS, SHOULD STAY IN THE
ADULT SYSTEM.
NOW, ONE OF THOSE DEFENDANTS
HAS FIVE PREVIOUS ENCOUNTERS
WITH THE LAW.
JUDGE STEPHEN SAID THAT IF YOU
LOOK SIMPLY AT THE NATURE OF
THE CRIME, THE HORRIFIC NATURE
OF THIS OFFENSE, IT WOULD ARGUE
FOR ALL OF THESE 15-YEAR-OLDS,
STAYING IN THE ADULT SYSTEM,
WHERE THEY COULD FACE MUCH MORE
SERIOUS MULTIS.
LAST HALLOWEEN, THE LAST DAY OF
FOOTBALL PRACTICE, THEY
ALLEGEDLY INVADED THE FRESHMAN
LOCKER ROOM,ONE FRESHMAN, WITH
A BROOMSTICK,  AND TRIED TO
WRITE THREE MORE KIDS.
THE LATEST DEFENDANT, ALLEGEDLY
ATTACKED ALL FOUR OF THE
VICTIMS, AND LAUGHED, AND EGGED
ON THE OTHER ATTACKERS.
THIS WAS NOT A PRANK, HAZING,
BOYS HORSING AROUND, THAT THE
PROSECUTOR.
IT WAS GREAT, AND MULTIPLE
ATTEMPTED .>> IT WAS