>> Announcer: TODAY ON AN
ALL-NEW "DR. PHIL."
THEY ARE ENGAGED TO BE MARRIED.
THE BEAUTIFUL BLOND TYING THE
KNOT WITH HER MILITARY VET.
TWO WEEKS AFTER THE ENGAGEMENT,
INSTEAD OF FIGHTING FOR OUR
COUNTRY, HE DECIDED TO FIGHT
CRIME AS BATMAN.
>> I'M NOT CRAZY.
I'M NOT DELUSIONAL.
I'M BATMAN.
>> Dr. Phil: HE WENT TO BED AS
GIOVANNI AND WOK UP AS BATMAN?
>> THIS IS NOT SOMETHING THAT
NORMAL PEOPLE DO.
>> Dr. Phil: ARE YOU
UNCOMFORTABLE TO NOT HAVE YOUR
MASK ON?
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE I'M ME
RIGHT NOW.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU'RE SAYING I'M
THE REAL BATMAN.
THERE'S NO BATMAN.
IT'S A CARTOON CHARACTER.
>> DR. PHIL: LET'S DO IT!
>> HAVE A GOOD SHOW, EVERYBODY.
>> DR. PHIL: THIS IS A SAFE
PLACE TO TALK ABOUT HARD THINGS.
>> STAND BY, I'LL COUNT YOU
DOWN.
>> DR. PHIL: TODAY WILL BE A
CHANGING DAY IN YOUR LIFE.
>> FIVE, FOUR --
>> DR. PHIL: I'M NOT GIVING UP
ON YOU.
[CHEERS & APPLAUSE]
>> Dr. Phil: WELL, MY GUEST,
KALAN, WROTE TO ME DESPERATE FOR
HELP AFTER HER FIANCE DECIDED TO
TAKE HIS CAREER PATH FOR
FIGHTING FROM OUR COUNTRY TO
FIGHTING CRIME ON THE STREETS
DRESSED AS A SUPER HERO.
ALL RIGHT.
HANG ON.
TAKE A LOOK AND WE'LL TALK.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO YOU ARE,
WHAT YOU WANT.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A FIGHT, I
CAN TELL YOU THAT I HAVE THE
SMOKE.
I ALSO HAVE A SET OF SKILLS,
SKILLS THAT I HAVE ACQUIRED OVER
A VERY LONG CAREER.
IF YOU ACCEPT THE FIGHT NOW THAT
WILL BE THE END OF IT.
I WON'T LOOK FOR YOU, I WILL NOT
PURSUE YOU, I WILL NOT FIND YOU.
IF YOU DON'T, I WILL STRAIGHT
BODY YOUR BITCH ASS.
WHY SO SERIOUS?
BECAUSE I'M BATMAN!
>> Dr. Phil: KALAN SAYS THAT SHE
HAS LOVED HER FIANCE WHO NOW
ONLY ANSWER TO GOOSE WAYNE
BADMAN SINCE SHE WAS 14 YEARS
OLD.
SHE DON'T KNOW HOW SHE CAN MARRY
HIM AS LONG AS HE BELIEVES AND
HE TRULY BELIEVES HE'S A SUPER
HERO AND REFUSES TO LEAVE THE
HOUSE WITHOUT HIS MASK OR EYE
MAKEUP.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> MY FIANCE BELIEVES HE'S A
REAL-LIFE SUPER HERO.
>> FIGHTING CRIME.
>> HIS REAL NAME IS GIOVANNI.
>> THAT IS NOT THE NAME THAT
DEFINES ME.
MY NAME IS GOOSE WAYNE.
>> I REFUSE TO CALL HIM GOOSE.
I CALL HIM G.
HE BELIEVES HE'S A SUPER HERO.
ONE DAY HE BOUGHT A MASK.
>> I WEAR GLOVES, A BELT AND
KEEP ITEMS IN MY POCKET HERE.
>> HE BOUGHT A SUIT AND THEN A
GRAPPLING HOOK CAME.
>> MY PANTS, KNEE PADS.
MIGHT BE KEVLAR.
>> THIS IS NOT JUST FOR
ATTENTION.
HE'S A 24-HOUR SUPER HERO.
>> THIS IS REAL LIFE.
THIS IS NOT A FAIRY TALE.
>> SOMETIME I'M EMBARRASSED TO
BE SEEN WITH HIM.
G WEARING THE MARKET HAS HURT
OUR SEX LIFE.
>> WHEN I'M SLEEPING NEXT TO HIM
WITH THE MASK, HE SOUNDS LIKE
DARTH VADER.
I THINK HE LOOKS LIKE A RACCOON.
>> I PREFER THE MASK OVER THE
RACCOON FACE.
>> G DOES PATROL HIS
NEIGHBORHOOD LOOKING TO FIGHT
CRIME.
>> RIGHT NOW I'M GOING TO THE
GAS STATION.
GOING TO SEE IF THERE'S ANY
TROUBLE OVER THERE.
I MIGHT COME BACK WITH SOME
BEERS.
>> HE'S BEEN IN REAL FIGHTS.
>> WHAT'S UP, GOTHAM?
LOOKING FOR THE VILLAIN.
WHO IS NEXT?
>> HE'S DRIVEN UPWARDS OF TWO
HOURS TO FIGHT SOMEONE THAT LOOK
LIKE THE KER.
HE'S LOST ALL OF THE FIGHTS.
IF G WANTS TO GET MARRIED WITH
THE MAKEUP OR THE MASK ON,
THERE'S NO CHANCE I WILL GO
THROUGH WITH THAT.
>> IF YOU WANT TO MARRY ME, YOU
HAVE TO MARRY BRUCE WAYNE.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO LET HIM
LOOKING LIKE A FOOL IN FRONT OF
MY FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
>> Dr. Phil: ALL RIGHT, KALAN,
GOOD TO MEET YOU.
REALLY GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU'VE KNOWN HIM
SINCE YOU WERE 14.
>> YES.
>> Dr. Phil: AND HE WAS FOUR
YEARS IN THE MILITARY?
>> YES.
>> Dr. Phil: FROM 14, 15, 16 ON
UP, HE NEVER SHOWED THIS
BEHAVIOR.
>> NO I'VE KNOWN HIM A LONG
TIME.
HE'S BEEN THE NORMAL MAN THAT
I'VE KNOWN UNTIL PROBABLY LATE
JULY OF THIS YEAR AFTER WE GOT
ENGAGED.
>> Dr. Phil: THIS IS HIM BEFORE.
A HANDSOME LOOKING HEALTHY GUY.
SERVED IN THE MILITARY.
YOU MAKE A HANDSOME COUPLE.
AND THEN HERE YOU ARE
AFTERWARDS.
WHAT HAPPENED ALONG ABOUT THAT
TIME?
ANYTHING YOU CAN POINT TO?
>> NO.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
I'M HOPING YOU HELP ME FIGURE
OUT WHAT IS.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'VE SEEN THIS
BEFORE, IF IT'S COMMON.
>> Dr. Phil: ONE DAY HE WENT TO
BED AS GIOVANNI AND WOKE UP AS
BATMAN?
>> NO.
IT WAS THIS VERY GRADUAL
PROCESS.
IT'S PEAKED NOW.
SO IT'S BEEN LIKE THIS THREE OR
FOUR OF HIM DEVELOPING THIS THIS
SUPER HERO CHARACTER.
IT'S NOT A JOKE TO HIM.
>> Dr. Phil: AND IT'S NOT A JOKE
TO YOU.
>> I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW HO TO
TAKE IT.
THIS IS SUCH A UNIQUE SITUATION
THAT I'VE NEVER HAD TO DEAL
WITH.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT NORMAL
PEOPLE DO.
THEY DRESS UP AND PUT ON MAKEUP
AND A COSTUME AND PARADE AROUND.
>> Dr. Phil: AND YOU KNOW OF NO
PARTICULAR EVENT, NO DEATH IN
HIS FAMILY, NO FIRING FROM A
JOB, NO DRUG ACTIVITY THAT
CORRESPONDS WITH HIM STARTING
THIS PROCESS?
>> NO.
>> Dr. Phil: AT FIRST, YOU
WEREN'T PARTICULARLY CONCERNED
ABOUT IT.
IT WAS JUST KIND OF A HOBBY OR A
GOOF OR SOMETHING HE WAS DOING.
>> YEAH.
I THOUGHT HE WAS DOING IT TO BE
FUNNY.
>> Dr. Phil: LET ME ASK YOU
THIS.
DO YOU HAVE A STANDARD HERE?
IF HE SAYS THIS IS WHO I AM,
THIS IS WHO I'M GOING TO BE,
WHAT I INTEND TO DEVOTE MY LIFE
TO, I WILL FOREVER CONTINUE
THIS, WOULD YOU MARRY HIM?
>> DEEP DOWN I WANT TO SAY YES,
THIS IS THE MAN I WANT TO BE
WITH, BUT AT THE SAME TIME, I'M
MAKING ACCOMMODATIONS FOR HIS
LIFESTYLE AND I DON'T FEEL LIKE
HE'S DOING IT FOR ME.
>> Dr. Phil: I'M CURIOUS HOW
MANY YOU'RE WILLING TO ENABLE
THIS AND YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE
BETWEEN THAT AND ME.
>> I WANT IT TO FIZZLE OUT.
I UNDERSTAND IT'S GOING TO BE A
PROCESS TO GET HIM BACK TO --
>> Dr. Phil: IF THIS IS
DELUSIONAL.
THEN THAT NEEDS TO BE DEALT WITH
AND NEEDS TO BE TREATED.
ONE OF THE THINGS I WOULD HAVE
TO ASK YOU IN ORDER TO HELP YOU
IS THAT YOU NOT BECOME PART OF
THE DELUSIONAL FABRIC AND ENABLE
HIM BY GOING ALONG WITH THIS
BECAUSE THAT GIVES HIM A FALSE
MESSAGE.
IN FACT, YOU HAVE GONE ALONG
WITH THIS SOME NOT KNOWING
WHETHER IT'S A GAME OR A PHASE
OR WHATEVER.
>> YES.
SO IN THE BEGINNING STAGES, HE
GOT THE HARLEY QUINN COSTUME
AND -- AGAIN, WHEN I THOUGHT IT
WAS NOT SERIOUS AND A JOKE, I
WOULD PLAY ALONG.
ONCE I FOUND OUT WHAT IT WAS, I
JUST -- I COULDN'T ANYMORE.
>> Dr. Phil: YEAH, BY THE WAY,
I'M NOT FAULTING YOU FOR THAT.
BECAUSE YOU GO ALONG TO GET
ALONG, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> Dr. Phil: THEN IT GETS TO A
POINT WHERE ENOUGH IS ENOUGH AND
TOO MUCH IS TOO MUCH.
IS THAT WHERE YOU ARE?
>> YES.
I'VE BEEN THERE A COUPLE MONTHS
NOW.
>> Dr. Phil: THAT'S WHAT I'M
SAYING.
I NEED TO KNOW IF YOU'RE WILLING
TO SAY I'M NOT GOING TO CONTINUE
TO PRETEND THAT I'M MARRIED TO
BATMAN BECAUSE THERE IS NO
BATMAN!
IT'S A CARTOON CHARACTER.
>> WE KIND OF GET IN THIS
CONVERSATION AND IT GOES ROUND
AND ROUND IN A CIRCLE.
>> Dr. Phil: THAT WON'T HAPPEN
TONIGHT.
[APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT.
CON
COMING UP, WE'RE GOING TO MEET
THE MAN THAT CAUSE HIMSELF
BATMAN.
HE SAYS NONE OF HIS 95,000
INSTAGRAM FOLLOWERS HAVE SEEN
HIM UNMASKED.
TODAY HE SAYS HE'S WILLING TO
COME OUT WITHOUT HIS MASK
BECAUSE I SAID IT'S NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN, WON'T DO THAT.
BUT HE SAYS HE IS GOING TO WEAR
MAKEUP TO FEEL COMFORTABLE.
WE'LL MEET HIM NEXT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THE FIRST TIME I SAW MYSELF
IN THE MIRROR WITH THE MASK AND
THE MAKEUP, I FELT EMPOWERED.
THERE'S NO GOING BACK.
LEGALLY I WANT TO CHANGE MY NAME
TO GOOSE WAYNE BATMAN.
IF KALAN MARRIES ME, SHE SHOULD
BE MRS. BATMAN.
>> Announcer: TOMORROW, SHE HAS
A NIGERIAN BOYFRIEND SHE NEVER
MET.
>> Dr. Phil: WHY DOES YOUR
FAMILY THESE HE'S A SCAM?
>> BECAUSE OF THE SHOWS WITH
YOU.
>> Dr. Phil: HE CALLS YOU HIS
FAT FISH.
S THAT OKAY?
>> IT'S FINE.
I'M FAT.
>> Dr. Phil: MIGHT IT BE YOU'RE
HIS GREEN CARD?
>> I DON'T BELIEVE AWARD YOU
SAY.
>> Announcer: THAT'S TOMORROW.
THEN ON MONDAY.
>> WOULD YOU LIKE DR. PHIL TO
HELP YOU?
>> Dr. Phil: WHAT GIVES YOU
PERMISSION TO TAKE A BUTCHER
KNIFE OUT OF THE
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
When was the last time
you felt...
Free.
It's time to uncover
that feeling again.
With the compassion and
strength of a name...
Most accepted by top doctors
and specialists.
And the power of a card...
that opens doors in
all fifty states.
Giving you the freedom to love
to dream to dance
Like no one is watching.
CareFirst
Blue Cross Blue Shield.
Live fearless.
>> G HAS POSTED SOME OUTRAGEOUS
VIDEOS ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
>> WHERE IS MY GRAPPLING HOOK?
>> G LOOKS FOR VILLAINS TO FIGHT
ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
HE HAS LIT HIMSELF ON FIRE.
EASILY SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT TIMES.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT HIM.
>> [BLEEP]!
>> I WANT HIM TO STOP PRETENDING
AND BELIEVING THAT HE'S A SUPER
HERO.
>> OH [BLEEP].
>> AND TO BE MY NORMAL FIANCE
AGAIN.
>> Dr. Phil: KALAN SAYS SHE
WON'T LET HER FIANCE SHOW HER
FACE ON SOCIAL MEDIA BECAUSE SHE
DOESN'T WANT PEOPLE TO KNOW WHAT
SHE HAS TO DO FOR LOVE.
GOOSE SAYS HE'S A SUPER HERO AN
WITHIN HIS RIGHTS TO BE WHO HE
WANTS.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> I BECAME GOOSE WAYNE ABOUT
FIVE MONTHS AGO.
MY NAME IS GOOSE WAYNE, BROTHER.
>> ALL RIGHT, BROTHER.
>> KEEP THE WORLD SAFE.
>> THE FIRST TIME I SAW MYSELF
IN THE MIRROR WITH THE MASK AND
THE MAKEUP, I FELT EMPOWERED.
PEOPLE TAKE ME MORE SERIOUS.
I'M NOT CRAZY OR DELUSIONAL.
I'M JUST A GUY THAT CARES ABOUT
PEOPLE.
I HAVE FULLY EMBRACED MY BRUCE
WAYNE PERSONA.
THERE'S NO GOING BACK.
>> DAY TO DAY I FIND PEOPLE
BREAKING THE LAW AND I TRY TO
BRING THEM TO JUSTICE.
I PHYSICALLY TRAIN TO BE BATMAN.
WIN FIGHTS.
>> MY BOXING GYM.
I BOOK HERE TODAY.
>> I'M DOING THE SOCIAL MEDIA
VIDEOS TO DRAW ATTENTION TO
GOOSE WAYNE.
IF I'M NOT ENTERTAINING, PEOPLE
WON'T LISTEN.
>> I HAVE BEEN VERY CAREFUL TO
NOT SHOW MY FACE ON SOCIAL MEDIA
BECAUSE I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE
PUBLICLY REVEALING MYSELF.
I'M DOING THIS FOR YOU.
LEGALLY I WANT TO CHANGE MY NAME
TO GOOSE WAYNE BATMAN.
IF KALAN MARRIES ME, SHE WOULD
BE MRS. BATMAN.
>> THAT'S NOT ON A OPTION.
>> I HOPE TO WEAR MY COSTUME ON
MY WEDDING DAY.
>> IT'S NOT HAPPENING.
>> SHE WANTS TO MARRY ME, YOU
MARRY ME FOR ME.
THIS IS ME.
THIS IS MY AUTHENTIC SELF.
>> THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Dr. Phil: ARE YOU
UNCOMFORTABLE TO NOT HAVE YOUR
MASK ON?
>> YES, SIR.
>> Dr. Phil: WHY IS THAT?
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE I'M ME
RIGHT NOW.
IT WOULD BE LIKE YOU'RE USED TO
DRESSING IN A CERTAIN ATTIRE AND
SOME PUTS YOU ATTIRE THAT YOU'RE
NOT USED TO AND YOU'LL BE
UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> NO, NOT REALLY.
I WEAR A SUIT BECAUSE IT SAYS
I'M INCREDIBLE.
I GUESS THAT GOES WITH THE
TERRITORY.
I GUESS I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN IN
THAT REGARD.
BUT AT WHAT POINT DID YOU DECIDE
THAT YOU WERE BATMAN?
>> I'VE ALWAYS HAD A DESIRE TO
PROTECT PEOPLE.
BEFORE I WAS BATMAN, I WORKED
LIKE ARMED GUARD-TYPE JOB WHERE
I GUARDED THINGS OF HIGH VALUE.
>> Dr. Phil: SO WHY NOT GO TO
THE POLICE ACADEMY WHERE YOU CAN
ACTUALLY PROTECT PEOPLE?
>> I THINK IT'S VERY STRUCTURED.
I'VE DONE THE STRUCTURE AND I
DON'T LIKE IT.
MIGHT SEEM LIKE I DON'T SERVE
MUCH OF A PURPOSE NOW TO OTHER
PEOPLE, BUT I'M -- I BELIEVE I'M
STILL LIKE IN MY INFANCY OF WHAT
I DO.
>> Dr. Phil: I WORK WITH LAW
ENFORCEMENT TO THE POINT THAT I
BLEED BLUE.
BELIEVE YOU ME, STRUCTURE IT IS
NOT.
YOU'RE OUT THERE ON THE MOVE,
HAVING TO MAKE SNAP DECISIONS
EVERY DAY.
LIFE OR DEATH.
THERE'S NOTHING STRUCTURED ABOUT
IT OTHER THAN YOU HAVE TO SHOW
UP AT A CERTAIN TIME.
>> THAT KIND OF ENVIRONMENT IS
JUST NOT FOR ME.
I LIKE TO DO MY OWN THING.
>> Dr. Phil: SO THIS REALLY
ISN'T ABOUT HELPING PEOPLE.
IT'S --
>> IT IS.
>> Dr. Phil: WELL, NO, IF IT WAS
ABOUT HELPING PEOPLE, YOU WOULD
GET IN A POSITION TO MAXIMIZE
YOUR IMPACT OF HELPING PEOPLE.
TEN YEARS FROM NOW, IF WE SIT
DOWN AND SAY HERE'S THE IMPACT,
HERE'S THE NUMBER OF PEOPLE
YOU'VE HELPED, LIVES YOU'VE
SAVED, CRIMES YOU'VE FOILED, DO
YOU THINK IT WILL BE MORE AS
THIS CHARACTER OF BATMAN OR MORE
AS SOON IN LAW ENFORCEMENT OR
SOME TYPE OF SECURITY?
>> I THINK I HAVE THE POTENTIAL
TO REACH A LOT MORE PEOPLE IN
THE LONG RUN ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
>> Dr. Phil: HOW IS THAT GOING
TO WORK?
>> I HAVEN'T FIGURED IT OUT YET.
I FOCUS ON CYBER BULLYING THAT A
LOT OF PEOPLE DON'T KNOW EXIST.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU'RE SAYING
YOU'RE GOING TO BECOME AN
EDUCATOR?
>> POSSIBLY.
ALSO AN ENFORCER.
>> Dr. Phil: OKAY.
THAT IS CALLED ASSAULT.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT IS A CRIME?
>> RIGHT.
>> Dr. Phil: SO YOU'RE GOING TO
DO THAT AND THEN YOU'RE GOING TO
GO TO JAIL BECAUSE YOU GO OUT
AND PUT YOUR HANDS ON PEOPLE,
THAT'S ASSAULT.
>> RIGHT.
I DON'T ENFORCE ANYTHING THAT
SOMEONE IS NOT AGREEING TO SO
FAR.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU SAY ONE OF THE
FEW PLACES YOU CAN GO WITH YOUR
MASK ON IS YOUR LOCAL DOUGHNUT
SHOP.
YOU REALLY SEEM TO TAUNT THEIR
EMPLOYEES.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHY BATMAN ONLY
GOES OUT AT NIGHT?
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE IT'S TOO [BLEEP] HOT.
>> Dr. Phil: WHAT IS YOUR
OBJECTIVE THERE?
>> THAT WAS PROBABLY THE FIRST
MONTH I STARTED DOING WHAT I DO.
I HAD TO GET EYES ON TO LET
PEOPLE GET MY MESSAGE.
SO I HAD TO GO ABOVE AND BEYOND
FROM AN ENTERTAINMENT
STANDPOINT.
>> Dr. Phil: SO THAT WASN'T
REALLY TO HELP ANYBODY.
>> THAT PARTICULAR VIDEO, NO.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU'VE GOTTEN ON
SOCIAL MEDIA AND FOUND PEOPLE TO
FIGHT.
>> RIGHT.
>> Dr. Phil: TAKE A LOOK AT
THIS.
>> OH.
OH, OH.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU DROVE TWO HOURS
TO FIGHT HIM?
>> YEAH.
>> Dr. Phil: WHY?
>> BECAUSE UP TILL THAT POINT,
PEOPLE WERE RIDICULING ME SAYING
I WAS JUST ALL TALK.
I WANTED TO SHOW EVERYONE THAT
IT'S NOT ALL TALK.
>> Dr. Phil: HOW DOES THAT HELP
PEOPLE?
>> PEOPLE KNOW THAT I'M NOT ALL
TALK.
WHEN I SAY I'LL PULL UP, I'LL
PULL UP.
THAT DEMONSTRATES THAT.
>> Dr. Phil: COMING UP, GOOSE
SAYS THAT HE'S EXCITED TO MARRY
KALAN BUT HE DOESN'T HAVE A
PAYING JOB AND RIGHT NOW REFUSES
TO GO THROUGH LIFE WITHOUT HIS
MASK HAHN AND HE'S GOING TO WEAR
IT GOING DOWN THE AISLE OR HE
WON'T GO DOWN THE AISLE.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT WHEN WE
COME BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
>> IT'S ABSOLUTELY DISGUSTING.
>> IT'S ONE OF THE WORK HAZARDS.
>> Announcer: COMING THIS
FEBRUARY --
>> I'M 64 YEARS OLD.
MY FIANCE IN NIGERIA IS 34 YEARS
OLD.
>> Dr. Phil: WHY DOES YOUR
FAMILY THINK HE'S A SCAM?
>> BECAUSE OF THE SHOWS HERE
WITH YOU.
>> Dr. Phil: HE CALLS YOU HIS
FAT FISH?
THAT'S OKAY?
>> IT'S FINE.
I'M FAT.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> Announcer: REAL ISSUES.
>> Dr. Phil: HE'S GONE FROM
HIGH-ACHIEVING PROFESSIONAL TO
LIVING IN HER TRUCK AND ALL OF A
SUDDEN SPEAKING WITH A BRITISH
ACCENT.
>> I HAD MY STROKE.
WHEN I WOKE UP, I HAD FOREIGN
ACCENT SYNDROME.
>> SHE SAYS SHE CAN SPEAK TO
BERRIES.
>> NO.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY YOU FOCUS
ON THIS.
>> I FOCUS ON THE TRUTH.
>> Dr. Phil: PEOPLE THINK YOU'RE
MAKING THIS UP?
>> I DO.
>> Dr. Phil: I DON'T.
>> Announcer: UNTHINKABLE.
>> Dr. Phil: WARNING.
TODAY'S SHOW IS WHAT I CONSIDER
THE MOST HEINOUS AND DESPICABLE
THING PERPETRATED BY A PARENT.
>> I WAS MY DAD'S SEX SLAVE.
>> Dr. Phil: AS UNIMAGINABLE AS
THIS STORY IS, YOU HAVEN'T HEARD
THE WORST OF
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
>> SINCE WE'VE BEEN ENGAGED, G
HASN'T HAD A JOB.
WHEN I ASK HIM WHAT HE'S GOING
TO DO, HE SAYS "BABY, I'M
BATMAN".
>> I WOULD GET A REAL 9 TO 5 JOB
IF THEY LET ME BE BATMAN.
>> BATMAN IS NOT A REAL JOB.
IT'S A FICTIONAL CHARACTER.
>> Dr. Phil: KALAN WORKS TWO
JOBS AND IS SO BUSY, SHE CAN
ONLY VISIT HER FIANCE ON
WEEKENDS WHEN SHE MAKES A
TWO-HOUR DRIVE TO HIS PLACE.
NOW, YOU SPENT FOUR ■YEARS IN TE
MILITARY, RIGHT?
>> YES, SIR.
>> Dr. Phil: THAT IS PROVIDING A
SERVICE.
THAT DOES IMPACT PEOPLE AND IT
DOES IMPACT EVERYONE OF US, ME
INCLUDED.
SO SINCERELY, THANK YOU FOR YOUR
SERVICE.
>> THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Dr. Phil: ARE YOU DELUSIONAL?
DO YOU SUFFER FROM A MENTAL
ILLNESS?
DO YOU THINK YOU DO?
>> IT'S VERY UNDERSTANDABLE THAT
THIS SEEMS LIKE I'M MENTALLY
DILUTED.
I STRONGLY OPPOSE THAT VIEW.
>> Dr. Phil: YEAH.
SEE, I'M PROBABLY THE LEAST
JUDGEMENTAL PERSON THAT I'VE
MET, AT LEAST.
I THINK EACH TO HIS OWN.
IF YOU WANT TO RUN AROUND
DRESSED UP AS BATMAN, KNOCK
YOURSELF OUT IF IT DOESN'T HURT
ANYBODY.
THE PROBLEM IS, I THINK IT DOES.
I THINK IT HURTS THE WOMAN THAT
YOU LOVE AND ALSO CHEATS SOCIETY
OUT OF YOU.
I MEAN, LIKE YOU SAID, YOU SPENT
FOUR YEARS IN THE MILITARY AND
NOW YOU JUST CHECKED OUT.
I CONSIDER, DOES HE HAVE A
MENTAL ILLNESS, IS THIS A
DELUSIONAL DISORDER?
LET'S LOOK AT WHAT THAT MEANS.
IT'S JUST A NONSCHIZOPHRENIC
INDIVIDUAL THAT EXPERIENCING
NONBIZARRE DELUSIONS.
THEY OFTEN SOCIALIZE AND
FUNCTION NORMALLY AND GENERALLY
DO NOT BEHAVE IN AN ODD OR
BIZARRE MANNER.
SO YOU KIND OF DON'T FIT THERE
BECAUSE YOU ARE BEHAVING IN WHAT
WOULD BE AN ODD MANNER, RIGHT?
>> DEPENDS.
>> Dr. Phil: LET'S LOOK AT
NORMAL VERSUS ABNORMAL.
NORMAL, IF YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
BEHAVIOR, DOES NOT INTERFERE
WITH HEALTHY FUNCTIONING AND
PURSUIT OF GOALS.
AND ABNORMAL INTERFERES WITH
HEALTHY FUNCTIONING AND PURSUIT
OF GOALS.
AND DOING THIS DOES INTERFERE
WITH PURSUIT OF GOALS.
IT'S NOT GETTING YOU WHAT YOU
WANT IN LIFE.
SEEMS TO ME LIKE IT'S PRETTY
SELFISH.
>> I THINK I'M PURSUING MY GOAL
OF INSPIRING PEOPLE.
>> IS IT SELFISH?
>> IT MAY BE.
IN REGARDS TO HER.
>> WELL, SHE MATTERS.
>> SHE DOES MATTER.
>> RIGHT?
>> YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL,
WAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU MIGHT FIND THIS
A PRETTY HARD ACT TO REPLACE.
>> AND I DO A LOT FOR YOU.
LONG DISTANCE RELATIONSHIP IS
HARD ENOUGH.
TO ADD THIS ELEMENT OF WHATEVER
THIS IS ON TOP OF IT, IT'S EVEN
MORE CHALLENGING.
SO --
>> Dr. Phil: SO YOU WORK TWO
JOBS.
>> I DO.
>> Dr. Phil: AND YOU DRIVE TWO
HOURS TO SEE HIM.
WHEN YOU GET THERE, WHAT
HAPPENS?
>> WE JUST STAY AT HOME.
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY HOW CAN I GET
ANYWHERE.
>> Dr. Phil: WHEN YOU GET THERE,
DOES HE HAVE HIS BATMAN MASK ON?
>> MOST OF THE TIMES.
IF HE DOESN'T, HE LOOKS LIKE
THAT.
>> Dr. Phil: AND HE HAS A BATMAN
SUIT.
>> HE DOES.
>> Dr. Phil: DOES HE WASH THIS
SUIT?
>> NO.
IT HAS COFFEE, BEER, SWEAT.
INSIDE OF HIS MASK IS
DISGUSTING.
>> THERE IT IS THERE.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU SAY HE HAS A
FUNGUS --
>> YEAH.
THAT WHITE PATCH IS NOT A
SUNBURN OR DRY SKIN.
IT'S A FUNGUS.
HE TRADE TO PUT HIS MASK IN MY
PURSE AND I GRABBED IT AND IT'S
SLIMY.
>> IT'S SWEAT.
>> IT'S DISGUSTING.
>> IT'S ONE OF THE WORK HAZARDS
I GUESS YOU'LL CALL IT.
>> Dr. Phil: COMING UP, GOOSE'S
DAD SAYS THERE'S THINGS FROM HIS
CHILDHOOD THAT MAY HAVE SOME
CONNECTION TO HIS CURRENT
CHOICES AND BEHAVIORS.
SO WE'LL HEAR FROM HIM NEXT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> I REMEMBER AS A KID,
HALLOWEEN, I WANT TO BE
SUPERMAN.
I DON'T GO WITH A CAPE AND TRY
TO FLY.
THIS IS ABNORMAL.
HE CAN GET HURT TRYING TO DO
THIS THING.
>> Announcer: I'M STARTING A
SERIES WHERE I'M TALKING ABOUT
FILLING IN THE BLANKS IN YOUR
LIVES.
I WANT YOU TO GET AN EDGE IN
YOUR LIFE.
THE ONLY PERSON YOU HAVE TO
CONTROL TO MAKE A HUGE CHANGE IN
YOUR LIFE IS YOU.
WHAT I WANT YOU TO DO IS START
LIVING BY DESIGN.
I WANT YOU TO HAVE A DEFINITION
OF WHAT SUCCESS IS IN YOUR LIFE.
I WANT US TO COME AWAY WITH A
PLAN THAT YOU CAN GET EXCITED
ABOUT.
>> Announcer: SUBSCRIBE
Feel the clarity of
non-drowsy Claritin
and relief from
Symptoms caused
by over
200 indoor
and outdoor
allergens.
Like those
from buddy.
Because stuffed
animals
are clearly no substitute
for real ones.
Feel the clarity.
And Live Claritin clear.
>> WHEN G BECAME THIS SUPER
HERO, HE ALSO BOUGHT ME A
COSTUME.
HE WANTED ME TO ROLE PLAY AS
HARLEY QUINN.
>> WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU HOW
TO [BLEEP] WORKOUT.
BATMAN AND HARLEY QUINN STYLE.
>> SHE USED TO BE IN MY VIDEOS.
EVERYTHING WAS COOL.
SHE NEVER COMPLAINED.
>> I THOUGHT HE WANTED TO MAKE
FUNNY VIDEOS.
BUT HE TOOK IT SERIOUSLY.
I WASN'T ON BOARD ANYMORE.
I STOPPED ROLE PLAYING.
>> Dr. Phil: KALAN SAYS THAT HER
HARLEY QUINN PAGE IS PRIVATE AND
SHE'S NEVER SHOWN HER FACE
BECAUSE SHE'S EMBARRASSED OF THE
WAY THE VIDEOS HIGHLIGHTED HER
BODY IN SLOW MOTION.
GOOSE'S DAD SAYS HIS SON IS 100%
LEGITIMATELY ACTING LIKE GOOSE
WAYNE ALL THE TIME AND THIS IS
NOT A STAGED PERSONA FOR THE
INTERNET.
HE ASKED ME TO HELP HIS SON.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> I'M A LITTLE CONCERNED WITH
GOOSE WAYNE, MY SON, GIOVANNI
GOES BY THAT NAME.
HE'S OBSESSED WITH BEING A SUPER
HERO CHARACTER.
HE HAS HIS MASK ON ALL THE I'M
TOO.
HE DRESSES LIKE BATMAN.
HE FEEDS THE HOMELESS AS BATMAN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IS WRONG WITH
HIM.
THERE'S HEROS EVERY DAY, BUT
DEFINITELY NOT DRESSED UP IN A
COSTUME.
THIS KID NEEDS HELP.
THANK YOU, DR. PHIL.
>> Dr. Phil: JOINING US VIA
PHONE RIGHT NOW IS YOUR FATHER,
RINALDO.
>> MY CONCERN IS FOR MY SON, AND
ALSO KALAN.
I DON'T THINK IT'S HEALTHY.
>> Dr. Phil: IS THERE ANYTHING
FROM HIS CHILDHOOD THAT COULD
EXPLAIN HIS BEHAVIOR?
>> I REMEMBER BETWEEN 8 AND 10
YEARS OLD, HE WAS SITTING IN THE
BACK OF THE VEHICLE.
HE WAS TALKING.
I ASKED HIM WHO ARE YOU TALKING
TO?
HE SAID HE'S TALKING TO HIS
FRIEND, MICHAEL.
HE SAID I'M TALKING TO A
UNIVERSITY WHERE THERE'S A
PSYCHOLOGIST THERE.
HE SPENT SOME TIME WITH THEM AND
SAID THIS COULD BE NORMAL AMONG
KIDS.
SOMETIMES THEY DO THAT.
I DON'T KNOW WHY HE PICKED
BATMAN.
I CAN REMEMBER AS A KID,
HALLOWEEN, I WOULD WANT TO BE A
SUPER HERO.
BUT HE CAN GET HURT TRYING TO DO
THIS THING.
>> Dr. Phil: WE HAVE TO TAKE A
BREAK.
I HAVE SOME QUESTIONS AND SOME
POINTS TO MAKE AND STAY WITH US
IF YOU CAN.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
>> JUST FEEL LIKE MARRIAGE IS
FOR BETTER OR FOR WORSE.
>> Dr. Phil: BUT YOU'RE NOT
MARRIED.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> Dr. Phil: BUT YOU CAN'T
CHANGE WHAT YOU DON'T
ACKNOWLEDGE.
IF HE'S NOT WILLING TO CHALLENGE
IT, THEN YOU HAVE A DECISION TO
MAKE, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> Announcer: TOMORROW ON AN
ALL-NEW "DR. PHIL."
SHE HAS A NIGERIAN BOYFRIEND
SHE'S NEVER MET.
>> Dr. Phil: HE CALLS YOU HIS
FAT FISH.
>> THAT'S
Pain wants to stop you...
like that's going to happen.
IcyHot. Icy to dull,
hot to relax.
Rise from pain. IcyHot.
I'm Ray and I quit smoking
with CHANTIX.
It's not easy.
You try to stop, you don't.
I needed help.
For me, CHANTIX did it.
CHANTIX, along with support,
helps you quit smoking.
CHANTIX, without a doubt,
reduced my urge to smoke.
When you try to quit smoking,
with or without CHANTIX,
you may have nicotine
withdrawal symptoms.
Some people had changes
in behavior or thinking,
aggression, hostility,
agitation, depressed mood,
or suicidal thoughts
or actions with CHANTIX.
Serious side effects
may include seizures,
new or worse heart or
blood vessel problems,
sleepwalking, or allergic
and skin reactions
which can be life-threatening.
Stop CHANTIX and
get help right away
if you have any of these.
Tell your
healthcare provider
if you've had depression
or other
mental health problems.
Decrease alcohol use
while taking CHANTIX.
Use caution when driving
or operating machinery.
The most common side
effect is nausea.
To have smoking behind me,
I feel like a million bucks.
Talk to your doctor
about CHANTIX.
>> WHEN I'M WALKING DOWN THE
STREET, I FEEL MORE PROUD THAN
WITHOUT THE MASK.
I FEEL MORE POWERFUL.
ONE OF MY GOALS IS TO BE WALKING
DOWN THE STREET AND PEOPLE SAY
THAT'S GOOSE WAYNE.
WE'RE SAFE.
>> I'M NOT EMBARRASSED.
I DON'T LIKE THE IDEA THAT THIS
IS HIS 24/7 LIFE.
>> WHY THE HELL YOU HAVE A MASK
ON?
>> THIS IS WHO I AM.
YOU SEE ANYTHING GOING ON, LET
ME KNOW.
>> IT'S ME AND YOU HERE ALL DAY,
DOG.
>> WHEN I MEET OTHER PEOPLE, IT
BOOSTS ME UP, MOTIVATES ME AND
WANTS ME TO KEEP DOING IT MORE.
>> Dr. Phil: DO YOU HAVE ANY
PROBLEM HISTORICALLY RECONCILING
THE FACT THAT THERE IS NO REAL
BATMAN?
THAT THIS IS A COMIC BOOK
CHARACTER?
>> I KNOW THAT BATMAN IS FAKE.
I KNOW THAT'S A CARTOON.
>> OKAY.
>> I DON'T LIKE CARTOONS.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU'RE SAYING I AM
THE REAL BATMAN.
>> THIS IS THE CLOSEST THING
THAT I RELATE WITH.
>> Dr. Phil: DO YOU FIND THAT
NARCISSISTIC OR SELF-IMPORTANT
TO DECLARE THAT YOU HAVE TO BE A
SUPER HERO AND THE REST OF US
JUST HAVE TO BE REGULAR PIONS?
>> NO.
>> Dr. Phil: WHY YOU?
WHY YOU TO BE THE SUPER HERO AND
I A REGULAR CITIZEN?
>> I DIDN'T ASK TO BE.
I GUESS I AM.
>> I WANT TO BE IN THE NBA BUT I
CAN'T DUNK.
>> IT WAS A CHOICE.
BEFORE I FELT JUST -- THIS.
I FELT IT.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT IT WAS.
I FOUND OUT WHAT IT WAS AND
THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING.
I MEAN, I DON'T -- I DO GOOD
THINGS.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
>> Dr. Phil: THEN WHY ALL OF THE
THEATER?
WHY DRAW ALL THE ATTENTION TO
YOURSELF AND WEAR THE CAPE AND
THE MASK?
WHY NOT JUST DOING SUPER GREAT
THINGS?
>> IT'S THE ONLY WAY THAT I CAN
REACH PEOPLE ON A LARGER SCALE,
PROVIDING SOME SORT OF
ENTERTAINMENT TO GET MY MESSAGE
ACROSS.
>> Dr. Phil: SO IF YOU COULD BE
A WELL-ACCOMPLISHED MOTIVATIONAL
SPEAKER WITHOUT THIS, YOU WOULD
BE BE SATISFIED WITH THAT?
>> POSSIBLY.
I CAN BE A MOTIVATIONAL SPEAKER
AS GOOSE WAYNE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY THIS WOULD
HINDRANCE ME.
>> Dr. Phil: IS IT POSSIBLE
PEOPLE WOULDN'T TAKE YOU
SERIOUSLY BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT A
GROWN MAN DRESSED UP LIKE A
COMIC BOOK CHARACTER?
>> MAYBE I WOULDN'T WEAR THE
SUIT.
>> Dr. Phil: WOULD YOU SETTLE
FOR THAT?
>> NO.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY IT
BREAKS MY HEART.
>> Dr. Phil: I'M SURE IT DOES.
YOU'RE GRIEVING THE FOR THE MAN
HE IS, NOT THE ONE THAT HE
WISHES HE WAS.
>> I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR 11
YEARS TO HAVE THIS MAN BY MY
SIDE.
I'M DOING ALL I CAN TO KEEP IT
THAT WAY.
>> Dr. Phil: BUT ONE OF THE
THINGS YOU CAN DO IS SET THE BAR
MUCH HIGHER THAN YOU'VE SET
AIN'T FIND OUT WHAT YOUR WORTH
IS TO HIM.
WOULD HE RATHER DRESS UP AS A
COMIC BACK CHARACTER OR BE BY
YOUR SIDE.
IF THE ANSWER IS HE WOULD RATHER
DRESS UP AS A COMIC BOOK
CHARACTER THAN SHARE HIS LIFE
WITH YOU, YOU'D RATHER NOW THAT
NOW THAN LATER, WOULDN'T YOU?
[APPLAUSE]
>> I FEEL LIKE MARRIAGE IS FOR
BETTER OR FOR WORSE.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU'RE NOT MARRIED.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
BUT I FEEL LIKE RIGHT NOW WE'RE
JUST AT FOR WORSE AND THE THINGS
COULD GET BETTER.
>> Dr. Phil: IF HE'S --
>> IF HE'S WILLING TO.
IF NOT, NO.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU CAN'T CHANGE IF
YOU DON'T ACKNOWLEDGE.
IF HE'S NOT WILLING TO CHALLENGE
IT, YOU HAVE A DECISION TO MAKE,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> Dr. Phil: WE'LL BE RIGHT
BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
>> I CURRENTLY HAVE ALL WEDDING
PLANS ON HOLD.
I HAVEN'T GOTTEN MY DRESS YET.
WE HAVEN'T GOTTEN ENGAGEMENT
Jimmy's gotten used to his whole
room smelling like sweaty odors.
Yup, he's gone Noseblind.
He thinks it smells fine, but
his mom smells this...
Luckily for all your
hard-to-wash fabrics...
...there's Febreze
Fabric Refresher.
Febreze doesn't just mask, it
eliminates odors you've...
...gone noseblind to.
And try Febreze
Unstopables for fabric.
With up to twice the fresh scent
power, you'll want to try it...
...again and again and maybe
just one more time.
Indulge in irresistible
freshness.
Febreze Unstopables.
Breathe Happy.
After walking six miles at
an amusement park...
Bill's back needed a
vacation from his vacation.
So he stepped on the
Dr. Scholl's kiosk.
It recommends our best
Custom Fit Orthotic
to relieve foot, knee, or
lower back pain.
So you can move more.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to move.
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
When I received the diagnosis,
I knew, whatever it takes,
wherever I have to go... I'm
beating this.
Breast cancer treatment is
continuing to evolve.
CTCA is definitely on the cusp
of those changes.
We really focus on taking the
time
with each individual patient
so they can choose the treatment
appropriate for them.
I empower women with choices.
It's not just picking a
surgeon.
It's picking the care team, and
feeling secure where you are.
Visit cancercenter.com.
Appointments available now.
>> IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE IN THE
LOS ANGELES AREA AND WANT TO
WATCH A LIVE TAPING, GO TO
drphil.com AND CLICK ON "BE IN
THE AUDIENCE."
TICKETS ARE FREE AND I HOPE TO
SEE YOU SOON.
>> Dr. Phil: I THINK YOU'RE A
VERY NICE GUY.
I THINK YOU'RE INTELLIGENT AND I
THINK THAT YOU ARE VERY CONFUSED
RIGHT NOW.
AND I THINK YOU HAVE FOUND A
PLACE TO KIND OF HIDE.
BUT IT'S AT THE EXPENSE OF YOUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH THE WOMAN YOU
LOVE AND THAT LOVES YOU.
IT AT THE EXPENSE OF BEING
FUNCTIONAL AND HAVING A JOB AND
I THINK IT'S GOTTEN TO THE
PEOPLE THAT IT DOES CONSTITUTE A
MENTAL MALADJUSTMENT.
AND I HAVE SOME GENTLEMEN THAT
I'VE ASKED TO COME HERE TODAY.
I WANT TO WELCOME DR. DANIEL
SUZUKI AND TREVOR.
THEY'RE FROM A HOSPITAL HERE IN
PASADENA.
THEY ARE A TOP PSYCHIATRIC AND
MEDICAL EVALUATION CENTER, AND
THEY SPECIALIZE IN MEDICALLY
SUPERVISED PATIENT CENTERED
TREATMENT APPROACHES FOR
EVALUATION AND TREATMENT.
SO I'VE ASKED THEM GENTLEMEN TO
JOIN US TODAY BECAUSE I'VE MADE
ARRANGEMENTS FOR HIM TO GO THERE
AND GET AN EVALUATION AND SEE
WHERE HE IS.
SEE IF HE CAN LEARN SOMETHING
ABOUT HIMSELF TO DETERMINE
WHETHER THIS IS A DISTORTION, A
CONFUSION OR DELUSION AND
WHATEVER AND CAN IT BE WORKED
OUT.
HE MAY GO THERE AND SAY NO, I
EXAMINED IT AND I'M COMPLETELY
COMFORTABLE WITH WHO AND WHERE I
AM AND THAT'S WHAT I'M GOING TO
DO IN MY LIFE.
THEN YOU'LL KNOW.
SO MY QUESTION IS, ARE YOU
WILLING TO GO AND BE EVALUATED
AND TAKE A LOOK AT THIS?
>> WE WOULD HAVE TO WORK
SCHEDULING.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE A JOB.    &-p]
>> I DON'T HAVE A -- LIKE A
GOVERNMENT JOB-TYPE DEAL.
I HAVE A DOG.
>> Dr. Phil: RIGHT.
>> I'M THE ONLY ONE THAT CAN
TAKE CARE OF MY DOG.
>> Dr. Phil: IF WE ARRANGE TO
KENNEL YOUR DOG, THAT WOULD BE
ALL RIGHT, WOULDN'T IT?
>> NO.
>> HE WOULDN'T BE TOO GOOD IN A
KENNEL.
>> I'M WILLING TO.
WE HAVE TO SCHEDULE OUT WITH MY
PARENTS.
LOGISTICS.
>> RINALDO, ARE YOU STILL THERE?
>> I'M STILL HERE.
>> Dr. Phil: YOU WOULD SUPPORT
THIS, WOULD YOU NOT?
>> I WOULD SUPPORT IT.
THE PROBLEM IS THAT EVERYBODY
HAS A DOG AND EVERYBODY WANTS TO
PUT IT OVER HERE.
>> Dr. Phil: I'M OFFERING AN
ABSOLUTELY TOP DRAWER, FIVE-STAR
CUTTING-EDGE EVALUATION AND
TREATMENT CENTER HERE.
I EXPECT YOU TO STEP UP AND
SUPPORT ME 100%, MY FRIEND.
[APPLAUSE]
IF THERE'S LOGISTICS TO WORK
OUT, I EXPECT THIS FAMILY TO
WORK OUT OUT IF I HAVE WORKED
OUT ALL THE RESOURCES THAT I
HAVE DONE AND BROUGHT THESE
PEOPLE HERE.
YOU GUYS ARE WILLING TO TRY TO
FIND THE BOTTOM, RIGHT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
CLEARLY YOU HAVE A BIG HEART TO
SERVE AND PROTECT PEOPLE BUT
SOMETHING HAS GONE WRONG HERE.
IF THEY COME TO OUR FACILITY, WE
HAVE A TEAM TO GET YOU ON THE
RIGHT PATH AND HELP YOU AND
KALAN FOR YOUR FUTURE IF YOU
WANT A FUTURE TOGETHER.
ABSOLUTELY.
>> Dr. Phil: I'M MAKING YOU THE
OFFER.
>> I WOULD REALLY HAVE TO TAKE A
STEP BACK AND LOOK AT MY
SCHEDULING.
>> Dr. Phil: OKAY.
THERE YOU HAVE YOUR ANSWER.
[APPLAUSE]
>> FOR 11 YEARS HE DOESN'T WANT
TO GET MARRIED AND HAVE KIDS.
I THOUGHT THAT THIS WHOLE
TRANSITION TO BATMAN WAS KIND OF
ODD TIMING WITH OUR ENGAGEMENT.
I WAS JUST HOPING THEY WEREN'T
RELATED.
BUT NOW I'M STARTING TO THINK
THAT IT IS RELATED.
>> Dr. Phil: MY THEORY IS
HIDING, RIGHT?
ESCAPING INTO FANTASY.
THAT CERTAINLY FITS WITH THAT
THEORY.
>> I CURRENTLY HAVE ALL WEDDING
PLANS ON HOLD.
I HAVEN'T GOTTEN MY DRESS YET.
WE HAVEN'T GOTTEN ENGAGEMENT
PICTURES BECAUSE I CAN'T MOVE
FORWARD.
>> WE CAN DO THE ENGAGEMENT
PICTURES.
>> Dr. Phil: ROBIN HAS A SIGN, A
LITTLE SIGN BY HER COMPUTER THAT
SAYS "IF YOU HESITATE, DON'T
PICK ME."
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> I'M NOT HESITATING AT ALL.
I DON'T THINK THAT SHE REALLY
HAS THAT BIG OF AN ISSUE WITH ME
BEING GOOSE WAYNE.
>> Dr. Phil: DO YOU SUPPORT HIM
GOING AND BEING EVALUATED AND
FINDING OUT WHAT'S GOING ON WITH
HIM HERE?
>> I DO AND I DON'T.
I REALLY DON'T THINK HE'S SICK.
I THINK THIS IS HIM TRYING TO BE
A BUM.
>> I'M NOT SICK AND I'M NOT A
BUM.
>> I HAVE TO DO ALL THE GROCERY
SHOPPING WHILE HE SITS IN THE
CAR BECAUSE HE CAN'T COME IN
LIKE THAT.
WHEN HE NEEDS BEER, I GET HIM
BEER.
WHEN HE NEEDS ANYTHING, I DO IT.
>> I GET A LOT OF MY OWN BEER,
TOO.
>> Dr. Phil: THAT IS
PATHOLOGICAL ENABLING.
THE FIRST STEP IS TO REALLY TAKE
A HARD LOOK AT THIS.
AS SOON AS I ASK, YOU CAVE.
My cholesterol is borderline.
I can worry about it, or do
something about it.
Garlique helps maintain healthy
cholesterol naturally,
and it's odor-free, and
pharmacist recommended.
Garlique
♪♪
This Valentine's Day
take a moment to
create a moment.
♪♪
Let love unfold when you
add your heartfelt message
to a new Hallmark Paper
Wonder card.
EUCRISA is an FDA approved
prescription ointment
for mild-to-moderate eczema.
And it's 100% steroid free.
Eligible patients may pay as
little as $10 per prescription.
Text SAVE to 47500.
Do not use if you are allergic
to EUCRISA or its ingredients.
Allergic reactions may occur at
or near the application site.
The most common side effect
is application site pain.
Ask your doctor about EUCRISA
and visit EUCRISA.com
to learn about savings.
>> DR. PHIL: WANT TO KNOW WHAT
IS COMING UP ON DR. PHIL, VISIT
OUR WEBSITE AND SUBSCRIBE TO OUR
E-MAIL NEWSLETTER.
YOU'LL GET WEEKLY UPDATES, LIFE
STRATEGIES AND EXCLUSIVE VIDEO
YOU WON'T FIND ANYWHERE ELSE.
>> PLUS ON DRPHIL.COM, YOU CAN
SEE SNEAK PREVIEWS OF UPCOMING
SHOWS.
LOG ON TODAY!
>> Dr. Phil: I'M GOING TO BE
REAL CLEAR.
YOU'RE WITH A MAN THAT IS
DRESSING UP LIKE BATMAN EVERY
DAY AND HE HAS NO INTENTION TO
CHANGE IT.
I'VE SAID I THINK IT'S A REAL
GOOD IDEA IF HE GOT EVALUATED TO
FIND OUT WHERE THAT COMES FROM.
YOU SAY WELL, I SUPPORT LOOKING
INTO THAT AND THEN AGAIN I
DON'T.
THAT IS PATHOLOGICAL ENABLING.
[APPLAUSE]
IF THAT'S WHERE YOU ARE, THEN HE
IS GOING TO CONTINUE TO DO WHAT
HE'S DOING.
AND I ASKED YOU BEFORE HE CAME
OUT HERE IF YOU WERE WILLING TO
DRAW THE LINE AND SAY I'M NOT
GOING TO SETTLE FOR THIS.
AND YOU SAID I WOULDN'T DO THIS
UNLESS HE WAS WILLING TO REALLY
WORK ON THIS AND CHANGE THIS.
BECAUSE I AIN'T MARRYING BATMAN.
SO THE FIRST STEP IS TO REALLY
TAKE A HARD LOOK AT THIS.
I ASK FOR YOUR SUPPORT.
YOU CALLED IT LIKE A PUP TENT IN
A WINDSTORM.
BOOM, YOU CAVE AFTER I ASK.
>> IT'S HARD TO THINK THAT HE'S
SICK.
I CAN'T IMAGINE MYSELF WITH
SOMEONE MENTALLY ILL.
>> Dr. Phil: MY ADVICE TO YOU IS
YOU'RE MAKING A SERIOUS, SERIOUS
MISTAKE BUT NOT SUPPORTING HIM
GOING AND GETTING HIMSELF
EVALUATED MENTALLY, EMOTIONALLY
AND PHYSICALLY.
[APPLAUSE]
MY ADVICE TO YOU FURTHER IS THAT
IF YOU MARRY HIM WHILE HE'S
PURSUING THIS POSITION IS
RIDICULOUS AND ABSURD AND WILL
BE A DISASTER FOR YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
AND YOU DESERVE MUCH, MUCH
BETTER.
BUT YOU GET WHAT YOU ASK FOR IN
THIS LIFE.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
[APPLAUSE]
MY ADVICE TO YOU IS THAT IF YOU
REALLY BELIEVE WHAT YOU BELIEVE,
YOU WOULD NOT BE AFRAID TO TAKE
A LOOK AT IT AND EVALUATE IT.
THE FACT THAT YOU'RE FEARFUL OF
IT TELLS ME THAT SOMEWHERE IN
THERE YOU KNOW BETTER.
AND I'M STEPPING UP AND OFFERING
YOU A VERY VALUABLE GIFT.
YOU ARE FOOLISH TO NOT SEIZE
UPON IT.
[APPLAUSE]
ALL RIGHT.
IN MY PODCAST THAT DROPPED THIS
WEEK, I TALK ABOUT THIS VERY
THING.
AND I TALK ABOUT HOW TO MAKE THE
RIGHT CHOICES AND SEIZE THE
RIGHT OPPORTUNITIES IN LIFE.
IT'S CALLED LIVING BY DESIGN.
YOU JUST SEARCH "PHIL IN THE
BLANKS" ON YOUR FAVORITE PODCAST
APP AND SUBSCRIBE.
IT'S FREE.
THE REASON I CALL IT LIVING BY
DESIGN, I THINK WE WAKE UP EVERY
DAY AND WE JUST REACT TO WHAT IS
PUT IN FRONT OF US.
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
I THINK WE NEED TO LIVE BY
DESIGN.
DO WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO DO WITH
YOUR LIFE, BUT DO IT ON PURPOSE.
LIVE BY DESIGN.
MAKE CHOICES ON PURPOSE.
THAT'S WHAT THIS WHOLE SERIES ON
THE PODCAST IS ABOUT.
I'M GOING TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
WHO YOU ARE, HOW YOU GOT TO BE
THERE AND HOW TO MAKE THE
CHOICES TO DO WHAT YOU WANT TO
DO WITH YOUR LIFE.
AND IT MAY BE A BIG CHANGE.
IT MAY BE MORE OF THE SAME BUT
MAY BE A BIG CHANGE.
BUT THIS IS SOMETHING THAT I'M
REALLY HAVING FUN DOING.
YOU CAN FIND IT ON
drphilintheblanks.com.
I WANT TO THANK ALL OF MY GUESTS
TODAY.
A SPECIAL THANKS TO DR. SUZUKI
AND TREVOR AND THE HOSPITAL.
IT'S A TOP NOTCH FACILITY.
FOR MORE INFORMATION AND TODAY'S
SHOW, GO TO drphil.com.
TELL US WHAT YOU THINK ON
FACEBOOK AND TWITTER.
GUYS, YOU MADE A BAD DECISION
HERE.
SO LONG.
[APPLAUSE]
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I DON'T THINK THERE'S
ANYTHING WRONG WITH ME TOO GO
TO THE HOSPITAL I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANYTHING OFF ABOUT ME.
>> I DON'T THINK IT IS SICK BUT
I DON'T THINK IT WOULD BE BAD
TO TAKE A LOOK.
>> IT WOULD BE LIKE DIFFERENT
IF I GO TO AN ORTHOPEDIC OR
SOMETHING IN MY ANKLE DOESN'T
HURT AT ALL.
>> LIKE GOING OUT SOMEWHERE AND
HAVING A ON.
>> THAT IS THE COMPROMISE I CAN
DO.
YOU WANT TO GO OUT COMING YOU
DON'T WANT TO DO THIS YOU WANT
THE OLD ME THEN WE GO OUT AND I
WON'T WEAR ANYTHING I WILL
DRESS NICE WHATEVER YOU WANT.
>> CALLING YOU BATMAN IS NO
LONGER AN OPTION IF YOU WANT TO
GET MARRIED.
WHAT IS SO FUNNY?
>> I'M WORKING.
I'M TRYING.
>> I WILL NOT GET MARRIED TO
THIS MAN UNTIL HE IS NOT BATMAN
ANYMORE.
>>> WE BEGIN WITH BREAKING NEWS
ON ANOTHER SCANDAL UNFOLDING IN
VIRGINIA.
WHILE YOU WERE AT WORK ANOTHER
RACIST YEARBOOK SURFACED, THIS
TIME FOR THE SENATE MAJORITY
LEADER OUTSIDE OF WILLIAMSBURG.
>> WOW ADDING INSULT TO INJURY
THE NEW YORK POST IS HOLDING UP
HIS HANDS.
VIRGINIA IS FOR LOSERS READS THE
PRESS PAGE.
THE VETERAN OF THE RICHMOND
STATEHOUSE, MIKE VALERIO IS
HERE.
FOR NEARLY A WEEK, DO WE SEE
ANYBODY RESIGNING AT ANY POINT.
>> NO.
WHAT A CHANGE THAT IS FROM
WHERE WE WERE AT THIS POINT
FRIDAY.
EVERYBODY IT SEEMS WILL
REASSIGNED THIS BECAUSE IF ONE
RESIGNS EVERYBODY WILL RESIGN
AS FOR POSSIBLY COULDN'T GET
WORSE ANOTHER RACIST,
INFLAMMATORY YEARBOOK.
THE VIRGINIAN PILOT PUBLISHING
THIS PHOTO FROM REPUBLICAN
SENATE MAJORITY LEADER'S 1968
YEARBOOK.
WITH BLACKFACE, CONFEDERATE
IMAGES AND SLURS.
NORMAL ONE OF THE HIGHEST
RANKING REPUBLICANS IN RICHMOND
AND HE HAD NO, TODAY.
>> SOMETHING THAT IS PAINFUL
FOR MOST OF US.
TO SEE, TO HEAR ABOUT THINK
ABOUT.
>> Reporter: U.S. SENATOR
KAMALA HARRIS WEIGHING IN NOT
ONLY ON THE SEARING SCANDALS
BUT ALSO NOW CALLING FOR A FULL
INVESTIGATION INTO SEXUAL
ASSAULT ALLEGATIONS AGAINST
JUSTIN FAIRFAX.
AS FOR GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM
HE IS STILL INTENT ON STAYING
IN OFFICE.
RESIGNATION CALLS ON RINGING
THROUGH RICHMOND. THE REVEREND
AL SHARPTON, NEAR THE STATE
CAPITAL TODAY.
>> I FLEW IN FROM NEW YORK TO
TELL YOU