[narrator]
Every year, spectacular seasons
transform our planet.
They're the driving force
of all life on Earth.
Bringing opportunities...
and huge challenges.
Spring bursts with new life.
[chirping]
But it's a race to grab
fleeting chances.
Summer is all about
glorious abundance.
But the heat can push animals
to their limits.
Autumn is nature's
great gold rush.
But competition is fierce.
Winter creates
a frozen wonderland.
And only the most resourceful
will survive.
In every corner
of the planet,
animals rise to overcome
the seemingly impossible...
and use extraordinary tricks...
to thrive against the odds
as the seasons create
the greatest shows on Earth.
Winter.
The sun's power is weakening.
It's getting colder
and darker.
The land is going
into suspended animation.
In this magical world,
animals are faced
with formidable challenges.
And when temperatures plummet,
the first big challenge
is keeping out the cold.
This extreme season
needs inventive solutions.
In the highlands of Scotland
a ptarmigan has to cope
with temperatures
approaching minus 30 degrees
centigrade.
So it grows more feathers
to keep the heat in.
It even has feathers
on its feet...
and its eyelids.
In North America,
a red fox keeps warm
by wrapping himself up
in his extra-thick tail.
Arctic foxes grow
one of the thickest coats
in the animal kingdom.
Her tiny ears and stubby legs
reduce heat loss.
And even the pads of her feet
have a covering of fur.
Even when it drops
to minus 70 centigrade,
she's quite comfortable.
But other animals
have more inventive ways
to stave off the cold.
Finland, on the arctic circle.
Temperatures here can fall
to minus 45 degrees centigrade.
The snow is so heavy
it can bend
the sturdiest of trees.
But among the drifts
lives one of the world's
smallest predators,
with a ruthless approach
to keeping warm.
A least weasel.
She's tiny,
barely 20 centimeters long.
She's grown a new white coat
for winter.
It keeps her almost invisible
in the snow.
Great for hiding
from predators,
but it's not thick enough
to protect her from the cold.
Even shivering can't generate
enough heat.
But this ingenious weasel
has a plan.
She starts by diving
under the snow.
Snow is 95% trapped air,
so it keeps the heat in
like a giant duvet.
There's a network
of tunnels.
But they're not hers.
They belong to voles.
Voles spend the winter
in their snow tunnels,
where they think
they're safe.
But with her skinny,
flexible body,
the weasel can easily
navigate the maze.
There's nowhere
for a vole to hide.
Spotted.
The vole is fast.
But the weasel is faster.
But there's more to this
than just a meal.
Once the weasel has eaten
the hapless vole,
she delicately
plucks its hair.
Then she weaves it
into her nest,
building herself
a furry cocoon.
Bed and breakfast...
in one convenient package.
Many animals must rely on their
wits to survive the bitter cold.
In the mountains
of central Japan,
winters can be brutal...
with some of the deepest
falls of snow in the world.
But there's a surprising animal
eking out a living here.
A monkey.
Aside from people,
these Japanese macaques
live further north
than any other primate
on Earth.
Their coats are
unusually thick,
to protect them from
the freezing temperatures.
Even when it's minus 20 degrees
centigrade,
a mom and her baby can cope.
But as the temperatures fall,
the monkeys need to find
extra calories to stay warm.
These are some of the cleverest
monkeys on the planet.
And they're so resourceful,
they'll never go hungry,
no matter how cold it gets.
They can eat almost anything.
And at this time of year,
nothing goes to waste.
As a last resort,
when all other food is gone,
they'll even eat
the bark of trees.
This is smarter
than it seems.
Just beneath the woody layer
is the sapwood,
where the tree stores
its precious nutrients.
It gives them just enough
calories to keep them going.
But this is not
their only clever trick
to get them through winter.
There's warmth
to be found here.
Japan is a land
of volcanoes.
Below the ground,
this volcanic activity
brings hot water
bubbling to the surface.
Even in the depths of winter.
It's a thermal spring.
And these ingenious monkeys
have learned
how to make the most of it.
Snow moneys have become
spa monkeys.
In their bath,
it's a comfortable 41 degrees
centigrade.
With constant warm water
to bask in,
these monkeys live a life
of leisure.
And the youngsters have plenty
of time to play.
Thanks to their
resourcefulness,
these clever monkeys
will survive,
no matter what winter
throws at them.
But when it comes
to fighting the cold,
this is the most challenging
place of all.
Antarctica.
The coldest place on Earth.
Temperatures can plummet
to minus 94 degrees centigrade.
You have to be a true specialist
to survive a winter here.
Emperor penguins.
At over a meter tall,
they're the largest penguins
in the world.
They've been out at sea,
fishing,
building up an insulating layer
of fat
nearly three centimeters thick.
And now they're about to face
the toughest winter on Earth.
Because penguins take so long
to raise their chicks,
they must start early.
And that means
incubating their eggs
through the planet's
deepest winter.
When she's laid
her single egg,
the female must return
to the sea to feed.
So it's over to the father
to incubate it.
All through winter.
He protects it
in a little pocket of skin
just above his feet.
He's now responsible for keeping
it safe and warm,
for nearly four months.
Just as the world's coldest
weather is closing in.
Antarctica is entering
six months of darkness.
Winter here is merciless.
[wind gusting]
The winds can top
190 kilometers an hour.
These are the darkest,
coldest,
windiest conditions
faced by any creature on Earth.
But through it all,
the emperor penguin dad
battles on.
He's still incubating
his precious egg...
perched on his feet,
just above the ice.
He and all the other fathers
have found an inventive way
to make it through
when times get really bad.
They come together
for the world's biggest huddle.
[wind gusting]
Penguins don't normally enjoy
being this close.
But they have no choice.
By crowding together as a team,
they can cut
heat loss by half.
After his stint on the edge
of the flock,
each penguin patiently queues
for his turn on the inside.
It's recently been discovered
that their huddle
is so effective,
the heat inside can build up
to around 40 degrees centigrade.
That's nearly
80 degrees warmer
than the temperature
on the outside.
So every now and then,
they must break formation
to cool down.
Throughout the male penguin's
four-month tour of duty,
the sun never rises once.
But just occasionally,
there's a glimmer
in the darkness.
Charged particles
from the sun
crash into the atmosphere
above the South Pole...
and blaze across the sky.
It's the southern lights.
The penguins barely
seem to notice.
But in a brutal season,
it's a moment of magic.
Winter is full of spectacle.
When the temperature drops
below minus six centigrade,
water vapor in the air
turns directly to ice.
These microscopic crystals
attract more and more
water droplets.
And they grow
into snowflakes.
In just one second, a million
billion are made by the clouds.
In 10 minutes, that's enough
snow for everyone on the planet
to build their own snowman.
Each flake is tiny,
but together they can blanket
the landscape,
turning it into
a wonderland.
It's a complete
transformation.
And even the animals
seem to enjoy the novelty.
[snarling and growling]
But for some,
there's a problem.
A thick blanket of snow
will hide their food.
So if they're going to find
anything to eat,
they have to come up
with some new tactics.
In North America,
a red fox relies on its ears
to listen for mice
scuttling around out of sight.
In Scandinavia,
a great gray owl also
has to hunt for hidden food.
It swoops in silently,
like a stealth bomber,
and then crashes through
the snow to snatch its victim.
In China, pandas have come up
with their own special technique
for clearing snow
off a bamboo branch.
Before they eat it,
they spin it around their
muzzles to brush it clean.
But some have switched
their diet altogether.
In the mountains
of southwest China,
where winter snow
lies a meter deep,
the Yunnan snub-nosed monkey
eats the lichen
that drapes the trees.
The lichen can survive
the freezing cold
of these high mountains.
This surprisingly
nutritious food
means the monkeys
can stay in these mountains
all year round.
But in some parts
of the world,
the heavy snows of winter create
an extreme challenge.
And survival
takes a bit of cunning.
In Yellowstone
in North America,
an otter family
has woken up
to discover their home river
is buried.
They don't have
anywhere to fish.
They're going to have
to relocate for winter.
In the same
neighborhood,
a coyote is having
similar difficulties.
Finding a meal around here
isn't going to be easy.
The otters have struck lucky.
There's an opening
in an icy lake.
And there are
still fish here.
It's fine for them.
But for the coyote,
life is trickier.
He's no fisherman,
but he is a master thief.
The otters
are suspicious.
The coyote would steal
their fish in an instant.
So they look for somewhere
to hide it.
The coyote might not be able
to see the otter,
but he can hear him.
He knows there's
a fish here somewhere.
Stashing it under the snow
won't fool a coyote.
He can smell it.
Bingo.
They're not called wily
for nothing.
As snow changes their world,
animals need to use every trick
in the book to find food.
[wind gusting]
But there is one animal
that uses it
to gain an advantage.
Wolves.
These Canadian wolves are some
of the biggest in the world.
They're opportunists,
and they'll travel
long distances
in the search for food.
Deep snow usually
makes moving difficult,
but sometimes it creates
an opportunity.
This wolf pair
is looking for a bison.
[snorting]
But they're hard to catch.
And finding them in this huge
wilderness is tough.
This is where the heavy snowfall
offers a clue.
The bison have left
deep tracks.
Tracks the wolves
can follow.
These two are working alone,
without the help of a pack.
And they're after
very dangerous prey.
Bison have sharp horns
and weigh a ton,
ten times the weight
of a wolf.
But the wolves
have no choice.
A bison would keep them fed
for a week.
And in winter,
you have to take a chance.
Finally, they pick up
fresh scent.
The herd must be close.
The hunt is on.
[whines and pants]
[panting]
The wolves move up a gear.
They can maintain this speed
for kilometers.
The bison are tiring.
The weaker ones fall back.
And the wolf couple
are getting closer.
A trip is all it takes.
Thanks to the snow,
the wolves are now a step ahead
of starvation.
And the rest of the herd live
to fight another winter battle.
Dealing with the challenge
of deep snow
forces animals
to raise their game.
But winter has another weapon
in its arsenal.
As days become
shorter than nights,
the temperature on the ground
begins to drop.
At zero degrees centigrade,
water turns to ice.
Little by little,
whole worlds transform.
At the poles,
even the sea freezes.
To survive the ice,
you need to be resourceful.
In North America,
a freezing river
is a challenging place
for a small bird.
But this tough little dipper
has extra thick
waterproof feathers.
It will happily dive
right under the ice
if it thinks there's something
worth eating.
In a frozen
Russian river,
sockeye salmon creep under
a ceiling of ice
to lay their eggs.
It might look crowded,
but here they're safe
from attack by birds of prey.
In northern Canada,
the winter freeze has created
a surprising opportunity.
This is a land
of lakes and bogs.
But in winter it's encased
in a sheet of ice,
two meters thick.
And there is one animal
that has managed to turn this
to its advantage.
Caribou.
Food is hard to come by,
so they must spend their winter
constantly on the move.
Despite their warm coats,
deep snow is a struggle
for them.
Trudging through it
saps their energy.
But the caribou
have discovered
that snow doesn't build up
on the ice,
because powerful winds
blow it away.
So now,
the lakes and rivers
become nature's very own
ice roads.
It means they can travel
more quickly,
saving precious energy.
But first, you must master
the technique.
The ice brings help
to caribou on the move.
But on the other side
of the world,
it's far less welcome.
In Antarctica, the freeze-up
has come in spectacular style.
In winter, the continent
doubles in size.
It's now bigger
than the U.S.A.
The giant lock-up causes
an urgent problem
for one inhabitant.
A Weddell seal.
As the sea around her freezes,
her breathing hole has begun
to freeze over too.
Without it,
she'll suffocate.
So she resorts to using
her teeth to keep it open.
But at least she has a retreat
from the icy world above.
The sea down here is a constant
minus 2 degrees centigrade.
That's over 50 degrees warmer
than it is at the surface.
And it's been like this
for 25 million years.
Beneath the layer of ice,
this enchanted kingdom
is protected
from the extreme
temperatures above.
It's a wonderland
of the strange and beautiful.
In this safe,
stable world,
life explodes.
But even here,
winter cold can crash the party.
As temperatures plummet
on the surface,
it triggers the growth
of something sinister.
This is a brinicle.
Super-cooled water
sinking from above,
forming a pillar of ice.
For the creatures of the seabed,
it's a stealthy finger of death.
A river of ice imprisons
everything in its path.
Even those that think they've
beaten the extremes of winter
can get caught out.
As winter takes hold,
there are even greater
tribulations coming.
Now animals not only have
to battle the conditions,
they also have
to battle each other.
For some,
it's over food.
For others,
it's over mates.
But winter raises
the stakes on everything.
In Russia,
black vultures,
the world's largest
birds of prey,
fight over scarce scraps
in the snow.
[squawking]
With their three-meter
wingspans,
it's all about
intimidation.
In Canada,
winter is the time
for young male polar bears
to tussle,
sorting out their status
without doing each other
serious damage.
But it's in South Georgia
in the South Atlantic
where the biggest
winter brawls happen.
[snarling]
Weighing in at four tons,
these elephant seals
are the world's largest.
It's a battle
of the big boys
to establish
who's in charge.
On the Canadian tundra,
there's another
battle looming.
And it's winter's ultimate
heavyweight fight.
Female caribou
are ready to mate.
It needs to be now,
so their young will be born
in early spring.
So the massive caribou bulls
must compete with each other
to father the calves.
The younger males
watch from the sidelines
as the heavyweights
eye each other up.
[grunts and snarls]
Serious fights are rare,
but when they happen,
they can be very dangerous.
But while this old bull
has been dealing with a rival,
the young bucks have been trying
their luck with his female.
He must break off his fight
and chase them away.
The younger males may be lighter
on their feet...
but his bulk means
he can muscle his way past.
Another rival steps in
with a challenge.
But the old bull
easily deals with him.
[grunting]
As the chase slows down,
he can finally impose
some order.
Now he's shown who's boss,
a look is all
that's needed.
Only when he's sure
he's made his point
can he claim his female.
The caribou may have a bruising
battle for their chosen females.
But for other animals,
competing for the right to mate
is even more challenging.
In a forest in Finland,
a black grouse is preparing
to put on a show.
[cooing]
It's the most important
performance of his life.
It will determine whether or not
he gets to breed.
Only one male will get
the chance to mate this year,
and that male will have
all the females.
The others
will get nothing.
With such high stakes,
the competition is intense.
[squawking]
The females begin to arrive,
and the dance-off
moves up a gear.
More and more males join in.
These birds can wait years
for an opportunity to mate.
Some will never
get the chance at all.
The females seem to have spotted
a potential winner.
It's half dance,
half handbags at dawn.
One last lunge is all he needs
to win the bout.
It's all over.
The loser slips away.
The best performer
is the strongest male,
and that's just what the females
are after.
His strength will be passed
to their chicks,
giving them the very best start
in life.
As the battles of winter
are settled,
there are tantalizing signs
that the season is changing.
For some animals, it's their one
chance to meet a partner.
A male polar bear has been
wandering the Arctic ice alone,
all through
the dark winter.
But as the sun returns,
it triggers his desire
to find a mate.
It's not an easy search.
In these vast wastes,
potential dates
are few and far between.
Eventually, he picks up
an unmistakable scent.
A female.
She could be 10 miles away.
So he follows her tracks.
There she is.
She's half his size,
so first-date nerves
are understandable.
He needs to win her over
gently.
He waits for her
to make the first move.
She leads him off
to higher ground.
Their relationship is brief.
And when they part company,
they will probably
never meet again.
[growls]
[wind gusting]
The wastes of the Arctic
might seem a tricky place
to find a mate,
but there are places that,
at first glance,
seem even more unlikely.
This is the Gobi Desert
in Mongolia.
It goes through
one of the greatest
seasonal temperature swings
on Earth.
In summer it can reach
50 degrees centigrade,
and in winter it's minus 40.
But these are perfect conditions
for a Bactrian camel
to practice his seduction
techniques.
Freezing winds have come
from the north.
And they have brought snow
to the desert.
This male suddenly has
a limitless water source.
He can eat the snow.
He's no longer tied
to sporadic water holes.
He's free to wander
huge distances
in the search
for new mates.
And when he finds a female,
he has an unusual way
of getting her attention.
He urinates on his legs.
Then, using his tail,
flicks it over his back.
[camel howls]
If he plays it right,
he might attract as many as 20
females before winter is over.
While camels are looking for
new mates in the Gobi Desert,
on the other side of the world,
older relationships
are about to be rekindled.
In Antarctica, the long cold
winter is coming to an end.
The sun has
finally returned.
The male penguin has survived
one hundred days
fighting the cold
to keep his precious egg warm.
He's lost nearly
half his body weight.
[all chirping]
As he enjoys the first warming
rays of sun,
he hears a familiar sound.
[squawking distantly]
Figures are appearing
on the horizon.
His mate has come back.
[all squawking]
There's a great
cacophony of calls
as couples find each other
in the throng.
Reunited, he can finally
introduce her to a new arrival.
[chirping]
All his effort
was worth it.
With enormous commitment,
these parents have given
their chicks
the very best start in life.
They're ready to join
the family firm
as the ultimate
winter survivors.
Winter brings huge challenges
to animals caught in its path.
Some have to battle
freezing temperatures.
Others have to struggle
to find food in the snow.
And some have to fight off
fierce competition.
[squawking]
But through it all,
animals find mates.
And some even
raise a family.
By being clever...
resourceful...
and brave...
you can survive
and even prosper...
no matter what winter brings.
ANNOUNCER: WASHINGTON'S
OLDEST COMMERCIAL DISTRICT,
KNOWN AS BARRACKS ROW,
IS TUCKED AWAY IN THE SOUTHERN
HALF OF CAPITOL HILL
NEAR EASTERN MARKET.
A SHORT ALLEYWAY OFF 8th STREET
LEADS DIRECTLY TO THE FRIDGE,
A UNIQUE ART GALLERY
THAT OPENED IN 2009.
MAN: THE FRIDGE IS MY BABY.
IT'S MY LIFE'S WORK.
IT IS AN ART SPACE
THAT I FOUNDED
TO REALLY HELP UNCOVER
YOUNGER ARTISTS--
ARTISTS WHO HAVE NOT NECESSARILY
EXHIBITED OTHER PLACES.
ANNOUNCER: THE FRIDGE IS
DEDICATED TO SHOWING THE WORK
OF STREET ARTISTS,
INCLUDING GRAFFITI
AND STICKER ARTISTS.
GOLDSTEIN: A LOT OF THE ARTISTS
THAT I'VE WORKED WITH
HAVE DONE WORK
OUT ON THE STREET,
MEANING LEGALLY
OR ILLEGALLY,
AS GRAFFITI ARTISTS
OR OTHER TYPES OF VANDALS
AND TAGGERS EVEN
WHO--WHO HAVE DEVELOPED
INTO INDOOR ARTISTS.
ANNOUNCER: IN ADDITION TO BEING
THE GALLERY'S OWNER,
ALEX GOLDSTEIN IS ALSO
AN ARTIST HIMSELF.
HE RECENTLY COMPLETED
HIS SECOND SOLO SHOW
AT THE FRIDGE,
WHICH FEATURED IMAGES
OF JOHN LENNON SPRAY-PAINTED
ON THE BACKS OF STREET SIGNS.
GOLDSTEIN: I'VE HAD THE BAD
HABIT OF PAINTING ON THE
BACKS OF STREET SIGNS
FOR MANY, MANY DECADES.
EVERYTHING IN MODERATION,
INCLUDING MODERATION.
SO, FOR THIS SHOW,
I DECIDED TO BRING THE
STREET INTO THE GALLERY.
ANNOUNCER: THE SHOW ALSO
GAVE HIM THE OPPORTUNITY
TO SHOWCASE WORK
BY HIS LATE FATHER.
GOLDSTEIN: MY DAD WAS A SCULPTOR
FOR A PERIOD OF HIS LIFE,
AND I'M GONNA BE DISPLAYING FOR
THE FIRST TIME EVER IN PUBLIC
SOME SCULPTURES THAT HE MADE.
AND SO THAT'S KIND OF,
I THINK, A TRIBUTE TO HIM
AND MY MOM, TOO.
STREET ART, YOU KNOW,
WHEN I WAS YOUNGER,
WASN'T CALLED THAT.
IT WAS JUST VANDALISM.
A LOT OF ARTISTS WERE PUTTING
UP ARTWORK ON THE STREET
AS A WAY TO GET IT SHOWN,
JUST TO SHOW TO EACH OTHER.
NOW THE BUILDING DEVELOPERS
HAVE BOUGHT ALL THOSE
BUILDINGS IN D.C.,
AND THEY ACTUALLY HIRE US-TYPE
STREET ARTISTS
TO ACTUALLY COME IN
AND DECORATE THE NEW PROPERTY,
WHICH IS REALLY AN
INTERESTING EVOLUTION.
I LIKE SEEING GRAFFITI.
IT'S A SIGN OF LIFE.
IT'S A SIGN OF PEOPLE TAKING
OWNERSHIP OF THEIR OWN SPACE.
AND WHILE I'M A BUILDING OWNER
AND I'D BE MAD
IF SOMEONE TAGGED
THE FRONT OF MY BUILDING--
WHATEVER. I CAN JUST
PAINT OVER IT
AND KNOW, ULTIMATELY,
IT'S NOT REALLY HARMFUL.
ANNOUNCER: THE FRIDGE IS OPEN
THURSDAY THROUGH SUNDAY
AND IS FREE TO THE PUBLIC.
ANNOUNCER: FOR OVER 50 YEARS,
BLUES ALLEY HAS HOSTED
WORLD-RENOWNED JAZZ ARTISTS,
SUCH AS DIZZY GILLESPIE,
SARAH VAUGHAN,
AND WYNTON MARSALIS.
TUCKED AWAY JUST OFF
WISCONSIN AVENUE IN GEORGETOWN,
THIS IS THE COUNTRY'S OLDEST
CONTINUING JAZZ SUPPER CLUB.
TONIGHT'S ARTIST
IS MIKE STERN,
A 6-TIME GRAMMY NOMINATED
GUITARIST
WHO USED TO PLAY IN THE BAND
OF JAZZ LEGEND MILES DAVIS.
YOU KNOW, I PLAY A LOT
OF DIFFERENT JAZZ CLUBS
ALL OVER THE WORLD,
BUT ONE OF MY FAVORITES
ANYWHERE IS BLUES ALLEY
IN WASHINGTON, D.C.
IN GEORGETOWN.
IT'S AN AWESOME CLUB.
IT HAS A--A BEAUTIFUL,
RELAXED KIND OF VIBE.
[PLAYING JAZZ MUSIC]
ANNOUNCER: BUT THE CLUB IS
ALSO FOSTERING THE NEXT
GENERATION OF ARTISTS
THROUGH ITS NON-PROFIT
BLUES ALLEY JAZZ SOCIETY.
JUST A FEW STEPS AWAY
IN GRACE EPISCOPAL CHURCH,
PROMISING YOUNG MUSICIANS
ARE REHEARSING.
MAN: 1, 2, 3, 4...
ANNOUNCER: THE BLUES ALLEY
YOUTH ORCHESTRA
IS LED BY MICHAEL BOWIE,
A RENOWNED BASS PLAYER.
BOWIE: WHAT I LOVE MOST ABOUT
TEACHING THE YOUTH ORCHESTRA
IS JUST THOSE
MOMENTS OF DISCOVERY
WHEN STUDENTS KIND OF GO,
"A-HA!" YOU KNOW?
THEY START TO
PUT THAT TOGETHER.
AND I'VE HAD SOME MOMENTS WHERE
I'VE--I'VE HEARD IT SO MUCH
IN THEIR MUSIC
THAT, YOU KNOW, IT ALMOST
BROUGHT ME TO TEARS.
EVERY TIME THAT I COME IN HERE,
I THINK I GAIN SOMETHING NEW
OR GAIN A DIFFERENT
APPRECIATION FOR SOMETHING
THAT I HADN'T HEARD BEFORE.
ANNOUNCER: LEARNING TO PLAY JAZZ
MEANS MORE THAN JUST READING
THE MUSIC.
BOWIE: UH, THE FACT IT'S NOT
BE-BOP, BUT BEBOP.
HA HA HA! AND ALL THOSE
LITTLE DIFFERENCES.
[SCATTING]
PICK UP END OF 92.
I'VE BEEN PLAYING
SINCE I WAS 6,
AND I STARTED JAZZ
WHEN I WAS 10.
AND THAT WOULD HAVE
A ... MARK,
[MUSIC PLAYING]
OR SOME-SOMETHING OVER IT
IF THEY WANTED YOU
TO GO BOP--YOU GOT THAT.
[HUMMING; WHISTLES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
HERE WE GO.
YEAH, MY BAD.
I GOT IT.
OK, EVERYTHING LEGIT.
A-1, 2...
BOWIE: I ADMIRE THESE STUDENTS
BECAUSE IT TAKES GUTS,
AND THEY HAVE GUTS.
YOU KNOW, IT REALLY DOES.
YOU COME IN AND YOU READ
TOP-LEVEL, PROFESSIONAL CHARTS
WHEN YOU'RE 14,
12 IN SOME CASES.
DUBESTER: AND THIS PROGRAM'S
HELPED ME DEVELOP SO MUCH
JUST 'CAUSE MICHAEL BOWIE
HAS BEEN SUCH A GREAT
MENTOR TO ME.
YOU KNOW, HE REALLY
TOOK ME UNDER HIS WING
WHEN I FIRST CAME IN.
ANNOUNCER: ON THIS AFTERNOON,
THE ORCHESTRA IS REHEARSING
FOR A MAJOR SHOW
TO TAKE PLACE ON THE MAIN STAGE
AT BLUES ALLEY.
[PLAYING JAZZ TUNE]
BOWIE: NOW IT'S UP TO THIS
NEXT GENERATION TO, UH,
TO MAKE MUSIC AS--AS VIABLE
AND SPEAKS TO PEOPLE.
THIS MUSIC IS
COMMUNICATIVE MUSIC.
IT'S ABOUT THE COMMUNITY.
[MUSIC ENDS]
[CHEERING]
MAN: LET'S HEAR IT FOR THE BLUES
ALLEY YOUTH ORCHESTRA.
[CHEERING CONTINUES]
ODS,"
MAN: LET'S HEAR IT FOR THE BLUES
ALLEY YOUTH ORCHESTRA.
FIND US ON FACEBOOK
AND AT WETA.ORG.
ODS,"
MAN: LET'S HEAR IT FOR THE BLUES
ALLEY YOUTH ORCHESTRA.
Be careful
with those pins.