We want them to
grow up stronger.
♪♪
>>> TONIGHT, MEGHAN MARKLE'S
BABY SHOWER IN NEW YORK.
>> BEAUTIFUL, MEGHAN.
>> THE POSH HOTEL, THE SECURITY.
INSIDE THE STAR-STUDDED
CELEBRATION.
BUT WHERE WAS HER MOM?
>>> THEN, LADY GAGA'S ENGAGEMENT
IS OFF.
NEW DETAILS BEHIND HER BIG
BREAKUP.
>>> PLUS, MIRANDA LAMBERT'S
SURPRISE WEDDING UNVEILED.
>> I'M OVERWHELMED AND THANKFUL.
>> WHY SHE KEPT IT A SECRET, WHY
HER HUBBY'S A HERO AND IS THERE
A BABY ON THE WAY?
>>> AND J-LO'S NEW CONFESSION.
>> THAT WAS NUTS.
>> THE ONE COMPETITION SHOW SHE
SAYS SHE WOULD NEVER WIN.
>> I DON'T THINK I WOULD HAVE.
>>> PLUS, I'M EXCLUSIVELY IN
LONDON WITH VICTORIA BECKHAM.
THEIR 20th ANNIVERSARY PLANS.
IS SHE REALLY SKIPS THE SPICE
GIRLS TOUR?
>> OH MY GOD.
>> AND HER FASHION FLASHBACK
THAT MADE HER GASP.
>> THAT WILL NOT BE MY "E.T."
LINE.
>> THIS IS "ENTERTAINMENT
TONIGHT."
>>> WE HAVE GOT BIG NEWS AND BIG
EXCLUSIVES.
WE ARE IN LONDON WITH VICTORIA
BECKHAM.
NEW YORK FOR MEGHAN MARKLE'S
BABY SHOWER, AND THEN THERE IS
THIS MIRANDA LAMBERT WEDDING
SHOCKER WITH A BABY IN THE MIX.
>> WE ARE ALL OVER THE GLOBE
TODAY.
>>> WE ARE IN FRONT OF A
DEVELOPING STORY THAT'S EVEN
BIGGER.
THIS JUST IN.
LADY GAGA AND HER FIANCE SPLIT.
♪ WE CAN WRITE A BAD ROMANCE ♪
>> A REP CONFIRMS THE NEWS.
THIS AFTER BREAKUP SPECULATION
BEGAN LAST WEEK.
CHRISTIAN CARINO WASN'T WITH
GAGA ON GRAMMY NIGHT.
NOR WAS THE ROCK OR A MENTION OF
HIM IN HER WINNING SPEECH.
>> THANK YOU FOR MY FAMILY.
>> THE PAIR WAS ENGAGED FOR 15
MONTHS AND HIT UP EVERY MAJOR
AWARDS SHOW TOGETHER, BUT ON
VALENTINE'S DAY INSTEAD OF
SHARING PHOTOS WITH HIM, GAGA
POSTED HER NEW TAT.
>>> NEXT UP, MEGHAN MARKLE'S
TAKING OVER NYC.
THE SEVEN-MONTH PREGNANT MEGHAN
CAUSED A RACKET.
SHE WENT TO AN ART MUSEUM.
>> OVER THE SHOULDER, MEGHAN?
>> SHE WENT TO A POSH HOTEL WITH
HER FRIEND, ABOUT GALE SPENCER.
SHE WAS SEEN HOLDING A GIFT.
MEGHAN'S GAL PALS GATHERED IN
NEW YORK REPORTEDLY FOR A BABY
SHOWER ORGANIZED BY THE DUCHESS'
CLOSE FRIEND, MARONEY.
MONDAY NIGHT, THE DUCHESS TRIED
TO LOOK INCOGNITO IN A LONG NAVY
COAT BY VICTORIA BECKHAM AND A
CAP OVER HER FLOWING LOCKS.
NOT THERE, HER MOTHER, DORIA
RAGLAND.
INSTEAD OF BEING IN NEW YORK,
TODAY SHE WAS SPOTTED IN LOS
ANGELES WALKING A DOG.
A ROYAL SOURCE TELLS "E.T."
MEGHAN'S CLANDESTINE NEW YORK
TRIP HAS BEEN FILLED WITH BUYING
BABY CLOTHES.
SHE WAS SEEING HER STATESIDE
GIRLFRIENDS BEFORE THE ROYAL
BIRTH.
MEGHAN IS BELIEVED TO BE FLYING
BACK TO THE UK MIDWEEK AND THEN
JETTING OFF TO MOROCCO WITH
HARRY FOR AN OFFICIAL VISIT, AND
THEN A SECOND BABY SHOWER IN
LONDON.
>> MOST PEOPLE THOUGHT BEING
PRETTY HEAVILY PREGNANT NOW THE
DUCHESS WOULDN'T BE GOING
OVERSEAS.
MEGHAN FELT VERY FIT AND VERY
WELL THROUGHOUT HER PREGNANCY.
UNLESS LIKE THE DUCHESS OF
CAMBRIDGE, NO MORNING SICKNESS.
>>> MIRANDA LAMBERT IS IN A NEW
RELATIONSHIP, AND SURPRISE.
THEY'RE HUSBAND AND WIFE.
AND THERE'S A BABY IN THE MIX.
MEET BRENDAN McLOUGHLIN.
MIRANDA MADE THE MARRIAGE
INSTAGRAM OFFICIAL OVER THE
WEEKEND, BUT OUR SOURCE SAYS THE
SECRET CEREMONY TOOK PLACE IN
JANUARY.
THAT'S AROUND TWO MONTHS AFTER
THEY FIRST MET.
HE WAS THERE WITH MIRANDA WHEN
HER GROUP PERFORMED THEIR SONG
IRONICALLY ABOUT DIVORCE
CALLED "GOT MY NAME CHANGED
BACK."
♪ GOT MY NAME CHANGED BACK ♪
>> HERE'S WHAT ELSE WE KNOW
ABOUT BRENDAN.
HE'S YOUNGER.
MIRANDA IS 35.
HE'S 27.
HE'S ALSO A NEW DAD.
"E.T." HAS LEARNED HIS CHILD
FROM A PREVIOUS RELATIONSHIP IS
A FEW MONTHS OLD.
A SOURCE CLOSE TO MIRANDA TELLS
"E.T." QUOTE, SHE NEVER FELT
READY TO HAVE CHILDREN UNTIL SHE
MET BRENDAN, AND NOW SHE'S
EXCITED TO BE A STEP-MOM.
IT'S GREAT PRACTICE FOR WHEN SHE
HAS A BABY.
♪♪
MIRANDA'S HUSH HUSH APPROACH
THIS TIME AROUND IS A FAR CRY
FROM HER FIRST MARRIAGE TO BLAKE
SHELTON.
>> I FEEL LIKE WHEN YOU ARE
REALLY OPEN ABOUT YOUR
RELATIONSHIP, THE LESS PEOPLE
DIG.
>> THEY SPLIT BACK IN 2015 AFTER
FOUR YEARS OF MARRIAGE.
ACCORDING TO OUR SOURCE, BLAKE
WHO HAS MOVED ON WITH GIRLFRIEND
OF OVER THREE YEARS, GWEN
STEFANI IS, QUOTE, VERY HAPPY
FOR HER.
>> NOW ONTO THE STORY THAT HAS
EVERYBODY SCRATCHING THEIR
HEADS, THE CRAZY TWISTS AND
TURNS IN THE JUSSIE SMOLLETT
INVESTIGATION.
AUTHORITIES ARE STILL TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT, WAS JUSSIE THE
VICTIM OF AN ATTACK OR DID HE
PLAN THE ENTIRE THING?
>> CHICAGO POLICE WANT TO
RE-INTERVIEW "EMPIRE" STAR
JUSSIE SMOLLETT ABOUT THE NIGHT
HE WAS ATTACKED.
FOR NOW, JUSSIE'S LAWYERS ARE IN
CHICAGO AND THEY SAY THEY WILL,
QUOTE, KEEP AN ACTIVE DIALOGUE
GOING WITH CHICAGO POLICE ON HIS
BEHALF.
THE FOLLOW-UP REQUEST COMES
AFTER A BOMBSHELL TWIST IN THE
CASE.
A SOURCE CLOSE TO THE
INVESTIGATION TELLS CBS NEWS,
TWO NIGERIAN BROTHERS TOLD
DETECTIVES SMOLLETT PAID THEM TO
PARTICIPATE IN THE ATTACK.
THEIR NAMES -- THAT'S THEM ON
THE SURVEILLANCE TAPE THE NIGHT
JUSSIE WAS ATTACKED.
OLA WORKED ON "EMPIRE" PLAYING A
PRISONER AND ABEL WAS HIS
PERSONAL TRAINER.
THAT'S HIM ON AN INSTAGRAM VIDEO
PRACTICING BODY BUILDING POSES
AS ONE OF JUSSIE'S SONGS PLAYS
IN THE BACKGROUND.
THE BROTHERS WERE INTERROGATED
LAST WEEK AFTER THEIR HOME WAS
RAIDED.
"E.T." NEWS PRODUCER IS IN
CHICAGO WITH THE LATEST.
>> THEY'RE INVESTIGATING A TIP
THAT ON THE NIGHT JUSSIE WAS
ATTACKED, HE WAS IN AN ELEVAOR
WITH THE TWO BROTHERS QUESTIONED
BY POLICE.
AND A SOURCE CLOSE TO THE
INVESTIGATION TELLS OUR CHICAGO
AFFILIATE WBBM THAT THE BROTHERS
TOLD DETECTIVES THEY REHEARSED
THE ATTACK WITH JUSSIE A FEW
DAYS BEFORE AND THE ACTOR PAID
THEM $3,500.
LAW ENFORCEMENT SOURCES ALSO
TELL THE STATION THEY BELIEVED
ONE OF THE BROTHERS PURCHASED A
ROPE USED IN THE INCIDENT AT
THIS HARDWARE STORE.
WEEKEND OF JANUARY 25th.
>> AS FOR JUSSIE, HE SFANDS
STANDS BY HIS STORY.
HIS ATTORNEY SAYS, QUOTE, HE HAS
NOW BEEN FURTHER VICTIMIZED BY
CLAIMS ATTRIBUTED TO THESE
ALLEGED PERPETRATORS THAT JUSSIE
PLAYED A ROLE IN HIS OWN ATTACK.
NOW IF JUSSIE'S FOUND GUILTY OF
FALSIFYING A POLICE REPORT, HE
COULD FACE FELONY CHARGES.
AT THIS POINT, I DON'T THINK
ANYBODY KNOWS WHAT TO THINK.
>> WE'LL HAVE TO WAIT FOR THE
FACTS BECAUSE THEY HAVE TO COME
OUT.
THEY HAVE TO COME OUT.
ALL RIGHT, KEV.
>>> LET'S MOVE ONTO SAD NEWS OUT
OF THE FASHION WORLD.
THE DEATH OF LEGENDARY DESIGNER,
KARL LAGERFELD.
HE PASSED AWAY TODAY AT THE AGE
OF 85, AND KARL LEFT HIS MARK ON
HOLLYWOOD.
>> I WOULD LIKE KARL LAGERFELD.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> THE ENVY OF STAR
FASHIONISTAS, KARL KNOWN FOR HIS
LONG PONYTAIL AND DARK GLASSES,
SPENT TIME IN HOLLYWOOD FOR THE
PAST 50 YEARS.
IN 1977, HE BECAME FENDI'S
CREATIVE DIRECTOR, BUT HIS
TAKEOVER OF CHANEL IN '83 SENT
HIM SKY HIGH INTO A BRAND HE
STILL LOVES TODAY.
>> SO ICONIC AND SO CLASSIC, BUT
YET IT'S STILL VERY RELEVANT AND
HIP AND EDGY.
>> VERY STRONG AND VERY
BEAUTIFUL.
>> NOT ONLY DID KARL CHANGE
CELEBS FASHION.
HE ALSO CHANGED THEIR LIVES,
HELPING LAUNCH CLAUDIA
SCHIFFER'S CAREER.
>> WHAT ARE WE WEARING?
>> CHANEL.
>> OH, OF COURSE.
>> TODAY CLAUDIA POSTED, HE
TRANSFORMED ME FROM A SHY GERMAN
GIRL INTO A SUPERMODEL.
HE IS IRREPLACEABLE.
>> NAOMI CAMPBELL, THANK YOU FOR
TAKING A CHANCE ON A SHY
16-YEAR-OLD GIRL.
>> EVERY JOURNEY WE GO ON.
>> BACK IN 2012, BRAD PITT WAS
KARL'S CHOICE TO SELL CHANEL
NUMBER FIVE TO WOMEN.
>> DID IT COME FROM A DREAM?
>> NO.
THE JOY.
>> LAGERFELD LEAVES BEHIND A
GODSON, HUDSON AND BELOVED
INSTAGRAM FAMOUS CAT CHOUPETTE,
BUT HE HAD A STRONG WORK ETHIC
AND SENSE OF HUMOR TO GO WITH
IT.
>> I'M JUST WORKING CLASS.
YES, YES, WORKING WITH CLASS,
HUH?
>>> COMING UP --
>> IT'S DONE, MAN.
IT'S DONE.
>> TYLER PERRY IS SAYING
GOOD-BYE TO MADEA.
WONDER HOW OPRAH FEELS ABOUT
THAT.
>> IS SHE COOL WITH YOU KILLING
OFF MADEA?
>>> THEN -- WE HAVE YOUR FIRST
LOOK AT "ROCKETMAN," BELTING OUT
THE HITS.
>>> AND POSH SPICE UNPLUGGED.
>> I WILL KEEP IT MINIMAL.
>>> AND WHY J-LO IS PRACTICING
Nick, Nick, we need a decision.
These days we all feel a little
anxious sometimes.
But if you could see inside my
mind;
You'll find I go to my happy
place.
See if we let tensions run the
show up here,
Then our bodies won't perform at
their best out here.
Wait, aren't we going to the
sound check?
Priorities.
So I'm partnering with Cigna,
To remind you that
how you're doing emotionally
affects you physically.
Go for your annual check-up
and be open with your doctor
about anything you're feeling.
Physically, and emotionally.
Body and Mind
Cigna. Together all the way.
>>> "E.T." ISN'T JUST ON THE
AIR.
WE'RE EVERYWHERE ON EVERY
PLATFORM EVERY DAY.
CHECK US OUT ON FACEBOOK,
♪♪
>>> HOW ABOUT THAT?
THAT'S TARON EGERTON BELTING OUT
HIS BEST "ROCKETMAN."
HE DOES ALL HIS OWN SING IN THE
MOVIE AND IT OPENS ON MAY 31st.
I THINK YOU'LL BE SURPRISED BY
HOW GOOD HE IS.
THE REAL ELTON JOHN IS ON HIS
FAREWELL TOUR.
>>> SPEAKING OF FAREWELL, TYLER
PERRY SAYS HE HAS MADE HIS LAST
MADEA MOVIE.
CALL ME A SKEPTIC, BUT I NEEDED
A LITTLE CONVINCING.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE THIS IS THE
END.
>> IT'S DONE, MAN.
IT'S DONE.
IT'S BEEN A GREAT RUN.
IT'S BEEN 20 YEARS OF JUST FAN
SUPPORT.
>> SO THEN WHY STOP?
>> I'M ALMOST 50 AND THERE IS
MORE I WANT TO DO.
>> I'M A REAL THUG.
>> IT'S BEEN A GREAT RUN.
11 MADEA MOVIES AND OVER HALF A
BILLION BOX OFFICE DOLLARS SO
FAR.
TYLER'S MENTOR, OPRAH IS A HUGE
FAN.
IS SHE COOL WITH YOU KILLING OFF
MADEA?
>> OPRAH IS COOL WITH WHAT'S
BEST FOR ME, AND IF THIS IS WHAT
I WANT TO DO, SHE'S RIGHT THERE
WITH ME.
>> ONE HALLMARK OF A TYLER PERRY
MOVIE, SHOOTING AT HIS OWN
STUDIO, HE KNOCKED THIS ONE OUT
IN NO TIME.
>> IT WAS A WEEK.
ONE WEEK.
>> HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
>> EVERYTHING IS ON THE STUDIO
ON THE LOT.
SO WE MOVE FROM HOUSE TO HOUSE.
WHERE IT WOULD TAKE ANOTHER
MOVIE TO MOVE IN EIGHT HOURS, I
CAN MOVE IN 30 MINUTES.
>> WHEN ARE YOU SLEEPING?
>> NOT MUCH IN THAT WEEK.
HIS AUNT MAYOLA WAS THE
INSPIRATION.
>> THEY'RE THE NC-17 VERSION OF
MADEA.
>> OH MY GOD.
WOW, MAN.
WOW.
>> COULD THERE BE SOME KIND OF
SPINOFF OUT OF THE MADEA
FRANCHISE?
>> YES.
WE'LL GO BACK TO THE '70s I'M
THINKING WITH A REAL ACTRESS
PLAYING HER ROLE.
>> HOW MUCH OF YOUR MOM AND YOUR
AUNT WILL BE IN THAT CHARACTER?
>> YOUNGER VERSIONS OF THEM.
THEY WERE HILARIOUS.
>>> STILL AHEAD, J-LO'S
DEFENDING A-ROD'S DANCE MOVE.
>> ALEX WINS.
>> WE'RE WITH THE "WORLD OF
DANCE" SPILLING NEW SEASON
SECRETS.
>>> PLUS --
>> WILL WE GET TO SEE INSIDE
YOUR CLOSET?
>> YOU DO GET TO SEE INSIDE MY
CLOSET AND HOW MESSY I REALLY
AM.
>> VICTORIA PLANNING A SECOND
WEDDING?
>> WILL YOU DO A VOW RENEWAL?
>>> CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED
BY --
Z35K8Z Z16FZ
Y35K8Y Y16FY
♪♪
>>> WELL, LOOK AT THAT
GOOD-LOOKING GROUP RIGHT THERE.
THE BECKHAM FAMILY INCLUDING
19-YEAR-OLD BROOKLYN'S MODEL
GIRLFRIEND SITTING FRONT ROW AS
MAMA VICTORIA'S FASHION LOW IN
LONDON.
>> REALLY COOL.
THEY LOOK FANTASTIC, AND YOU
KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S WHERE KELTIE KNIGHT GOT
AN EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW WITH POSH
SPICE.
>> HEY, GUYS.
WE'RE HERE IN LONDON WHERE
VICTORIA BECKHAM HAD HER HUGE
FASHION SHOW.
I'M SO EXCITED AND THE COOLEST
THING SITTING IN THE FRONT ROW
WAS ANNA WINTOUR WITH MATCHING
HAIRCUTS.
SO CUTE.
♪ I TELL YOU WHAT I WANT ♪
>> ANNA IS AN INSPIRATION FOR US
ALL BUT SOMEONE USED TO HAVE A
BOB AS WELL.
IT WAS ME.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE YOUR 20th
WEDDING ANNIVERSARY THIS YEAR.
WILL YOU DO A VOW RENEWAL WITH A
NEW DRESS?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
I DON'T THINK SO.
WE'LL PROBABLY JUST CELEBRATE
WITH THE KIDS.
DAVID IS SUCH A GREAT HUSBAND.
HE'S SUCH A GREAT DAD AND THE
MOST INCREDIBLE BUSINESS PARTNER
THAT ANYBODY COULD EVER WANT.
HE REALLY SUPPORTS ME IN WHAT I
DO.
>> I FOUND THE FIRST INTERVIEW
YOU HAVE EVER DONE WITH "E.T."
AND YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT HOW
YOU WERE NEWLY MARRIED.
>> WHAT WAS GREAT ABOUT OUR
WEDDING IS WE SPEND ALL THE TIME
TOGETHER.
>> OH MY GOD.
WHERE WERE MY EYEBROWS?
I WAS TAN, AND I HAD BLONDE
HAIR.
>> I HAVE GOT A FABULOUS OUTFIT
AND HAIRDO.
>> IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE THE SAME
PERSON.
WHERE WERE MY EYEBROWS?
>> WHO KNEW VICTORIA HAD A SASSY
SIDE?
SHE JUST LAUNCHED HER OWN
YOUTUBE CHANNEL WITH KATY
PERRY'S BFF.
HER FIRST POST, HER FASHION
SHOW.
>> IT'S THE BIGGEST SHOW I HAVE
DONE, AND THERE WERE MORE LOOKS
THAN I HAVE DONE BEFORE.
>> WHAT WON'T YOU DO?
>> LET'S BE HONEST.
I WANT TO GAIN FOLLOWERS AND NOT
LOSE THEM.
SO I WILL KEEP THE NUDITY
MINIMAL.
>> WILL WE GET TO SEE INSIDE
YOUR CLOSET?
>> YOU DO GET TO SEE INSIDE MY
CLOSET AND HOW MESSY I REALLY
AM.
THERE WILL BE SOME FAMILY
MOMENTS IN THERE AS WELL BECAUSE
MY FAMILY IS A HUGE PART OF WHAT
I DO.
>> OF COURSE, YOU KNEW I COULD
NOT SIT DOWN WITH THIS
44-YEAR-OLD MOM OF FOUR WITHOUT
ASKING IF THERE IS ANY CHANCE
SHE WILL REUNITE WITH THE SPICE
GIRLS.
YOUR FRIEND, MEL B. SAYS YOU
MIGHT BE HITTING UP WIMBLEY
STADIUM.
>> YEAH.
NO.
I COULDN'T DO IT AND I'M SO BUSY
DOING WHAT I'M DOING NOW, BUT
I'LL ALWAYS BE A SPICE GIRL AND
I'M VERY EXCITED TO SEE WHAT
THEY'RE GOING TO DO, BUT EVERY
TIME I DO AN INTERVIEW, I DON'T
WANT TO SOUND LIKE ABSOLUTELY
NOT.
I DON'T WANT TO BE MEAN IN ANY
WAY.
I LOVE THE IDEA OF IT, BUT THE
REALITY IS THAT NO.
IT WON'T HAPPEN.
THEY'LL BE GREAT.
♪♪
>> NOW TO ANOTHER STYLE ICON,
J-LO.
I WAS WITH THE "WORLD OF DANCE"
EXECUTIVE PRODUCER AND HER
FELLOW JUDGES AHEAD OF NEXT
WEEK'S SEASON THREE PREMIERE.
>> YOU HAVE TO ABSOLUTELY BRING
IT.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT.
>> THAT WAS NUTS.
>> WHEN YOU WERE YOUNG, DID YOU
HAVE THAT FEAR OR WERE YOU
JUST -- YOU WENT OUT THERE?
>> I THINK I WAS PRETTY
FEARLESS, LIKE, IGNORANCE IS
BLISS.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
I CAN FALL ON MY FACE AND IT'S
GOING TO SCAR ME FOR TEN YEARS.
YOU KNOW NONE OF THESE THINGS.
>> THE SHOW IS RAISING THE BAR.
CONTESTANTS HAVE TO SCORE AN 85
OUT OF 100 INSTEAD OF 80 TO MAKE
IT PAST THE FIRST ROUND.
WOULD A YOUNG JENNY FROM THE
BLOCK HAVE MADE THE CUT?
>> I WOULD LIKE TO THINK I
COULD, BUT I DON'T THINK I
COULD.
I DON'T THINK I WOULD HAVE.
>> AND WHILE THE DANCING IS
PRETTYING AMAZING, THERE IS
SOMETHING ELSE WE'RE LIVING FOR,
J-LO'S FABULOUS FASHION.
EVEN HER EXTENSIONS ARRIVED TO
SET IN STYLE.
IF ALL OF YOUR SIGNIFICANT
OTHERS GOT TOGETHER AND THEY
WERE HERE, WHO WOULD WIN?
>> OBVIOUSLY YOUR SIGNIFICANT
OTHER BECAUSE SHE'S A
PROFESSIONAL DANCER.
>> DEPENDS ON WHAT WE'RE
JUDGING.
JUDGING TECHNIQUE OR, YOU
KNOW --
>> PASSION.
>> COMMITMENT?
>> COMMITMENT IS PROBABLY MY
WIFE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW.
ALEX IS PRETTY COMMITTED.
>> COMPETITOR.
>> HE'S A COMPETITOR.
>> OH, ALEX.
STICK TO BASEBALL.
>> HE IS A GREAT BASEBALL
PLAYER.
LOOK.
A-ROD IS NOTHING BUT SUPPORTIVE
OF JENNIFER, ESPECIALLY WHEN IT
INCLUDES A STRIPPER POLE.
>> OKAY.
>> HE POSTED THIS VIDEO OF HER
REHEARSING FOR HER UPCOMING
MOVIE, "HUSTLERS."
SHE'LL PLAY A STRIPPER AND SHE'S
BRINGING WORK HOME.
THAT PORTABLE POLE IS IN HER
CRIB.
HOMEWORK IS OKAY.
>> NOT MAD.
>>> LET'S GO TO "THE BACHELOR."
COLTON WILL BE VISITING THE
HOMETOWNS OF THE FINAL FOUR AND
THAT WILL PROBABLY INCLUDE
HOMETOWN COOKING AS WELL.
FOOD IS ALSO AT THE TOP OF OUR
LIST FOR OUR FAVORITE "BACHELOR
IN PARADISE" COUPLES WHEN THEY
VACATION AND WE LEARNED THAT
WHEN WE TEAMED UP WITH SECRETS
REPORTS AND SPAS FOR UNLIMITED
LUXURY.
>> EVAN, CARLY.
FROM THE RED CARPET ROLLING IN
TO BREAKFAST FOR YOU GUYS.
>> OH MY GOD.
AMAZING.
>> ENRIQUE, AMAZING ROOM
SERVICE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU GUYS ARE THE SUCCESS
STORY
OUT OF REALITY TV.
WHAT IS THE SECRET?
>> WE'RE JUST DOING OUR OWN
THING IN NASHVILLE.
WE'RE NORMAL PEOPLE.
♪♪
>> GUYS, I CANNOT THINK OF A
BETTER PLACE TO HAVE LUNCH.
THESE VIEWS ARE UNBELIEVABLE.
AS WE HAVE BEEN ON THIS TRIP, I
HAVE NOTICED PEOPLE COME UP TO
YOU CONSTANTLY.
WHAT DO THEY ASK YOU MORE THAN
ANYTHING?
>> FOR PICTURES.
>> FOR PICTURES?
>> THE QUESTION WE GET IS, IS IT
REAL?
YEAH.
WE'RE HERE TOGETHER SO IT'S
REAL.
>> CHEERS, GUYS.
>> CHEERS.
>> THE SECRET TO YOUR
RELATIONSHIP IS FRIENDS FIRST.
THEN YOU FELL IN LOVE.
WHEN DID YOU KNOW THAT THINGS
HAVE TURNED ROMANTIC?
>> WHEN DID THEY TURN ROMANTIC
MUTUALLY?
WHEN DEREK TOLD ME.
>> ABOUT MY FEELINGS, YES.
>> LET'S GET YOUR SPECIAL NIGHT
OUT DINNER OVERLOOKING THE
WATER.
>> SO PRETTY.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> OH, STEAK AND LOBSTER.
PERFECT.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> THAT SURE LOOKS PRETTY.
I CAN EVEN ENJOY THAT WITH YOU.
>> NO, YOU WOULDN'T.
SHE'S A TOTAL LIAR.
WE WOULD CHOKE EACH OTHER BY THE
END OF THE NIGHT.
>>> COMING UP, WE ARE COUNTING
DOWN TO OSCAR SUNDAY WITH MUSIC
NEWS THAT WILL ROCK YOU.
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>> TRAVEL CONSIDERATIONS
PROVIDED BY --
>>> TOMORROW ON "E.T." IS 2019
THE YEAR OF RIHANNA?
>> THE SKY'S THE LIMIT.
NO RULES.
>> WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT NEW MUSIC
AND THE BIG SCREEN ROLE GIVING
US "A STAR IS BORN" VIBES.
>> I HOPE WE CAN REALLY PULL
THIS OFF.
>> TOMORROW ON "E.T.."
>>> HEY, COUNTRY MUSIC FANS LIKE
HER, SET YOUR ALARM FOR 5:50
PACIFIC.
>> I AM HERE FOR IT.
OF COURSE, THIS SUNDAY IS THE
ACADEMY AWARDS ON ABC AND NOW WE
KNOW THAT MOVIE'S BIGGEST NIGHT
WILL GET OFF TO A ROCKIN' START.
♪ WE WILL, WE WILL ROCK YOU ♪
>> QUEEN AND ADAM LAMBERT WILL
OPEN THE OSCARS TO
CELEBRATE "BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY'S"
FIVE NOMINATIONS.
DID YOU KNOW ADAM APPEARS IN THE
MOVIE?
THAT'S HIM AS THE TRUCKER WHO
CATCHES THE EYE OF FREDDIE
MERCURY.
>> ALSO PERFORMING, BETTE
MIDLER.
SHE WILL SING THE SONG, "THE
PLACE WHERE LOST THINGS GO."
VOTING FOR THE OSCARS CLOSED
TODAY.
IF YOU HAVEN'T VOTED, GUESS
WHAT?
>> TOO BAD.
>> THERE YOU GO.
SO GOOD.
>>
DOES YOUR CUSTOMERS
CONNECTING TO THE WIFI
EVER SLOW DOWN YOUR BUSINESS?
YES, IT DOES SLOW THINGS DOWN.
AGGRAVATING.
IT'S A NIGHTMARE.
SO OUR GIG-SPEED
NETWORK IS FAST.
AND WE GO BEYOND FAST BY
MAKING IT EASY TO CREATE
SEPARATE NETWORKS FOR YOUR
BUSINESS AND YOUR CUSTOMERS
AND EVEN CONTROL HOW MUCH
BANDWIDTH EACH OF THOSE GETS.
SO YOUR BUSINESS
WON'T MISS A BEAT.
THIS IS A BIG GAME CHANGER.
THIS IS THE NEW WAVE, AND
WHOEVER DOESN'T GET ON,
I THINK THEY WOULD
BE LEFT BEHIND.
WIFI PRO RUNS ON THE
GIG-SPEED NETWORK.
PAY JUST $49.95 A MONTH
FOR FAST INTERNET
AND GET A $300 PREPAID CARD.
COMCAST BUSINESS.
BEYOND FAST.
CHLOE:
What's it called?