>> I WOULD GO INTO BLACK AREAS
SO I COULD UNLEASH PHYSICAL
VIOLENCE.
>> LIAM NEESON ACCUSED OF BEING
A RACIST.
HOW HE'S GOING INTO DAMAGE
CONTROL AFTER ADMITTING TO A
REAL-LIFE REVENGE PLOT.
>> THIS WILL END YOUR CAREER,
LIAM.
>>> AND THE OSCAR CLASS PHOTO SO
STAR-STUDDED EVEN THE NOMINEES
ARE FANNING OUT.
>> CAN YOU NOT CAUSE UTTER
CHAOS?
>>> PLUS, LIVE FROM NEW YORK,
IT'S OPRAH.
HER LOVE FEST WITH MICHAEL B.
JORDAN.
>> NOTHING LESS.
>> AS OUR EXCLUSIVE TAKES TURNS.
WHAT HAS THESE BESTIES AT ODDS?
>> TAKE IT BACK.
>> NO, YOU TAKE IT BACK.
>>> AND WE'RE WITH PINK FOR HER
BIG HOLLYWOOD HONOR.
HOW HER KIDS STOLE THE SHOW.
>> I THINK THEY'RE JUST TERRIBLY
BORED AND THEY WANT TO GO HAVE
PIZZA.
>> THIS IS "ENTERTAINMENT
TONIGHT."
>>> LIAM NEESON HAS ONE OF THE
WORLD'S BIGGEST ACTION STARS,
BUT NOW HE IS FIGHTING TO CLEAR
HIS OWN NAME AFTER BEING ACCUSED
OF BEING A RACIST.
>> HERE'S THE DEAL.
IT ALL STEMS FROM A STORY HE
TOLD ABOUT ONCE BEING HELL-BENT
REVENGE, NOT UNLIKE HIS
CHARACTER IN THE "TAKEN" SERIES,
BUT LIAM IS NOT BACKING DOWN
FROM THIS EITHER.
>> I'M NOT RACIST.
>> LIAM WAS IN DAMAGE CONTROL
MODE THIS MORNING AFTER
HIS "GMA" SITDOWN.
HE HEADED TO "LIVE WITH KELLY
AND RYAN."
HE IGNORED THE PAPARAZZI.
>> THIS IS GOING TO END YOUR
CAREER, LIAM.
>> THERE WAS A BACKLASH AFTER
ADMITTING A REAL LIFE RACIST
REVENGE FANTASY.
HE PROMOTED HIS NEW MOVIE, "COLD
PURSUIT."
THE FILM IS ABOUT A FATHER
SEEKING REVENGE FOR HIS SON'S
DEATH WHICH LEADS TO HOW HE
SOUGHT REVENGE 40 YEARS AGO WHEN
A CLOSE FRIEND OF HIS TOLD HIM
SHE HAD BEEN RAPED.
>> I ASKED, DID SHE KNOW WHO HE
WAS?
WHAT COLOR?
SHE SAID, IT WAS A BLACK PERSON.
AND AFTER THAT, THERE WERE SOME
NIGHTS I WENT DELIBERATELY INTO
BLACK AREAS IN THE CITY, LOOKING
TO BE SET UPON SO THAT I COULD
UNLEASH PHYSICAL VIOLENCE.
AND I DID IT FOR -- I WOULD SAY
MAYBE FOUR OR FIVE TIME.
>> LIAM SAYS HE LEARNED A
VALUABLE LESSON FROM HIS
REACTION.
LESS THAN AN HOUR LATER, RYAN
SEACREST ASKED ABOUT THE
CONTROVERSY.
>> WHAT DO YOU TAKE AWAY FROM
IT?
WHAT DO YOU LEARN FROM IT?
>> THE NEED FOR DIALOGUE.
>> GOOD HE'S GETTING OUT IN
FRONT.
IT'S JUST A TOUGH SUBJECT TO
TALK ABOUT.
>> "VARIETY"'S JUSTIN KROLL SAYS
LIAM'S MOVIE STRATEGY MAKES
ACCEPTANCE, BUT AS FOR THE BOX
OFFICE IMPACT --
>> IT HAS A LOT OF COMPETITION
THIS WEEKEND WITH "LEGO MOVIE 2:
THE SECOND PART" AND "WHAT MEN
WANT."
IT'S HARD TO TELL.
>> LIAM HAS A SPECIAL SCREENING
OF HIS MOVIE TONIGHT IN NEW
YORK, BUT THE RED CARPET HAS
BEEN CANCELED.
THERE WILL BE NO PRESS ALLOWED.
>>> OPRAH WINFREY IS ALSO IN NEW
YORK RIGHT NOW.
SHE JUST GOT BACK FROM HER GIRLS
GETAWAY CRUISE WITH GAYLE KING
AND OUR NISCHELLE TURNER AND
NISCHELLE GOT THE SCOOP ON
TODAY'S STAR-STUDDED LIVE EVENT.
>> HEY.
MICHAEL B. JORDAN.
BRADLEY COOPER.
WE HAVE A BIG DAY AHEAD.
BRADLEY IS HAVING HIS MOMENT
WITH WHAT HE CREATED, AND IT
CERTAINLY IS A RISING STAR
MOMENT FOR MICHAEL B. JORDAN.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I'M THE KING NOW.
>> PLEASE WELCOME OPRAH WINFREY.
>> EARLIER TODAY IN TIMES
SQUARE, OPRAH'S LIVE THING
KICKED OFF WITH A SUPER VILLAIN.
>> WORLD DOMINATION.
NOTHING LESS.
>> IS THE WORLD RETIRE IN YOUR
VOCABULARY?
YOU'RE BUSIER THAN EVER.
>> NO.
I DON'T BELIEVE IN IT.
>> SHE HAS BARELY HAD A DAY OFF
SINCE "E.T." BOARDED THEIR
GETAWAY CRUISE.
THE VOYAGE WAS INSPIRED BY THEIR
FRIENDSHIP.
>> EVERYBODY SHOULD HAVE A GAYLE
AND I LOVE THAT PEOPLE COME AND
INTRODUCE ME BECAUSE EVEN THEY
SAY THIS IS MY GAYLE.
PEOPLE SAY USE THE TERM BEST
FRIEND LOOSELY.
BEST FRIEND MEANS YOU CAN SAY
ANYTHING.
>> YOU CAN SAY ANYTHING, BUT
THAT DOESN'T MEAN YOU ALWAYS
AGREE.
NISCHELLE SAW THAT AFTER ASKING
THIS QUESTION.
>> HAVE YOU SET GAYLE UP ON A
DATE?
WOULD YOU LET HER THE.
>> I DID TRY.
I DID TRY.
>> BHO?
>> WHO?
>> SERIOUSLY, WHO?
>> SHE KNOWS MORE PEOPLE -- I
DON'T GET IT.
>> I DO NOT KNOW MORE.
PEOPLE THAN YOU.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> I SOCIALIZE MORE THAN YOU,
BUT I DON'T KNOW MORE PEOPLE
THAN YOU.
>> NO.
YOU TAKE IT BACK.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> NO.
>> THAT IS SOME BFF STUFF RIGHT
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THERE.
>> THAT IS SOME BFF STUFF RIGHT
I LOVE THEM TOGETHER.
THERE.
>>> WELL, LET'S MOVE ON BECAUSE
I LOVE THEM TOGETHER.
THE OSCARS HAVE FINALLY MADE IT
>>> WELL, LET'S MOVE ON BECAUSE
OFFICIAL.
THE OSCARS HAVE FINALLY MADE IT
THIS YEAR'S SHOW ON THE 24th
OFFICIAL.
WILL NOT HAVE A HOST, AND
THIS YEAR'S SHOW ON THE 24th
YESTERDAY AT THE ANNUAL OSCAR
WILL NOT HAVE A HOST, AND
LUNCHON, WE LEARNED EVEN
YESTERDAY AT THE ANNUAL OSCAR
HOLLYWOOD SCHOOL KIDS GET STAR
LUNCHON, WE LEARNED EVEN
STRUCK WHEN IT'S TIME TO SMILE
HOLLYWOOD SCHOOL KIDS GET STAR
FOR THE HOLLYWOOD CLASS PHOTO.
STRUCK WHEN IT'S TIME TO SMILE
>> WHAT WAS THAT MOMENT LIKE?
FOR THE HOLLYWOOD CLASS PHOTO.
>> JUST SO MAGICAL.
>> WHAT WAS THAT MOMENT LIKE?
I WAS LUCKILY KIND OF AT THE END
>> JUST SO MAGICAL.
OF THE TOP TIER SO I COULD SEE
I WAS LUCKILY KIND OF AT THE END
JUST THE JOY.
OF THE TOP TIER SO I COULD SEE
>> REGINA WAS HAVING A BIG LAUGH
JUST THE JOY.
IN THE BACK.
>> REGINA WAS HAVING A BIG LAUGH
RIGHT IN FRONT OF HER WAS
IN THE BACK.
MELISSA McCARTHY.
RIGHT IN FRONT OF HER WAS
>> YOU KEEP TRYING TO TURN
MELISSA McCARTHY.
AROUND AND YOU'RE, LIKE, I'M
>> YOU KEEP TRYING TO TURN
GOING TO FALL.
GOD, I HOPE I DON'T GO DOWN.
I'LL TAKE 15 PEOPLE WITH ME.
>> LADY GAGA STRUCK A REGAL POSE
NEAR BRADLEY.
ALSO A BIG HUG FOR SPIKE LEE
FROM AMY ADAMS.
NEWCOMER, YALITZA APARICIO
BETWEEN FORMER WINNERS CHRISTIAN
BALE AND RACHAEL WEISS.
>> I HAVEN'T HAD THAT SINCE
GRADUATING FROM COLLEGE.
IT WAS HEARTWARMING AND SWEET.
>> GLENN CLOSE HIDING BEHIND
ALFONSO CUARON, AND RAMI MALEK
WITH A MISCHIEFOUS GRIN.
>> IT WAS GOOD TO SEE PEOPLE.
>> MELISSA'S DATE WAS HER MOM,
SANDY WHO WAS THERE FOR OUR
INTERVIEW TOO.
>> HI, MOM.
IT'S AMAZING TO DO THIS WITH
HER.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
THEY ARE INCREDIBLY SUPPORTIVE,
BUT THEY'RE, LIKE, EVERYTHING
YOU DO IS AMAZING.
IT WAS, LIKE, IF YOU WORK HARD
ENOUGH, WHY NOT YOU?
>> REGINA HAS PAID HER DUES AS
WELL.
WE PLAYED OUR INTERVIEW WITH HER
FROM BACK IN 1996.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY COMPLAINTS
AS FAR AS ANY CAREER HAS GONE.
>> WHO IS THAT LITTLE GIRL?
I WAS SOMEBODY'S MOTHER RIGHT
THERE.
>> YOU'RE SO SWEET.
>> BUT I LOVE --
>> AND THE VOICE.
THAT MADE ME CHEER UP BECAUSE I
FELT LIKE I WAS LOOKING AT A
LITTLE GIRL.
I HAVE COME -- I HAVE COME A
LONG WAY, BABY.
>> YES, YOU CERTAINLY HAVE.
I CANNOT WAIT TO SEE THE STARS
AT THE OSCARS.
BACK TO THE OSCAR PHOTO FOR A
SECOND, THERE WERE NOTABLE NAMES
MISSING LIKE EMMA STONE AND
OLIVIA COLEMAN.
EMMA IS SHOOTING "ZOMBIELAND 2,"
AND OLIVIA IS SHOOTING SEASON
THREE OF "THE CROWN," SO SHE'S
NOT THERE.
>>> MEANWHILE, HOLLYWOOD STILL
REELING AFTER THE SUDDEN PASSING
OF KRISTOFF ST. JOHN.
I SPOKE WITH HIS WIFE BECAUSE OF
THE TWO MEN SHE LOVED THE MOST.
HER SON, JULIAN, AND KRISTOFF
ARE GONE WAY TOO SOON.
SO MANY THOUGHTS SENDING THEIR
THOUGHTS AND PRAYERS, INCLUDING
KRISTOFF'S FRIEND AND FORMER
CO-STAR, SHEMAR MOORE.
>> I NEVER HAD A BROTHER, BUT
YOU WERE MY BROTHER.
YOU WERE MY MENTOR AND
INSPIRATION.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> THEY WERE INSEPARABLE WHEN
"E.T." HIT THE "Y&R" SET IN
1995, AND YESTERDAY SHEMAR
CAPTURED THIS SERIES OF
TRIBUTES, SLEEP EASY.
>> I WAS TRYING TO BE MODEST.
MY BROTHER IS NOT MODEST.
>> NO.
>> "Y&R" TELLS US KRISTOFF'S
LAST EPISODE WILL AIR TOMORROW
AND THEY WILL PAY SPECIAL
TRIBUTE TO HIM DURING FRIDAY'S
SHOW.
NOW NEW DETAILS IN JUSSIE
SMOLLETT'S ATTACK.
THE "EMPIRE" STAR WAS HESITANT
TO FILE A REPORT.
DETECTIVES STILL HAVEN'T I.D.'d
TWO PEOPLE OF INTEREST.
THE ABC AFFILIATE JUSSIE
REVEALED THE PRIMARY AGGRESSOR
WAS WEARING A BLACK MASK
CONCEALING HIS FACE AND HE
COULDN'T REMEMBER ANY OTHER
FEATURES.
>> YOU CAN'T LET HATE WIN.
>> TARAJI P. HENSON SAID HER TV
SON HASN'T BEEN BACK TO SET YET.
>> HE WILL BE ABSOLUTELY.
WE MISS HIM.
THAT'S HOW HE OPERATES.
>> SPEAKING OF LOVE, TARAJI OUT
PROMOTING "WHAT MEN WANT," IS
CELEBRATING A RELATIONSHIP
MILESTONE.
HER FIRST VALENTINE'S DAY
ENGAGED.
>> WHATEVER AGE YOU ARE, WHOEVER
YOU'RE COURTING, BE YOURSELF.
TELL THE TRUTH.
>>> COMING UP, KELLY CLARKSON,
TALK SHOW STAGE FRIGHT?
WITH JUST MONTHS UNTIL HER
DEBUT, KELLY'S PLAN TO BREAK
AWAY FROM HER FEARS.
>>> THEN --
>> STARTING CHEMOTHERAPY FOR
CANCER.
>> ABBY LEE MILLER IN THE FIGHT
OF HER LIFE.
SHOCKING NEW IMAGES FROM THE
"DANCE MOMS" STAR'S CANCER
BATTLE.
>>> AND WE CANNOT WAIT FOR THIS.
WHY YOU'LL SEE DOLLY AND KATY
TOGETHER REALLY SOON.
♪ JOLENE ♪
>>> BUT FIRST, JACKIE EVANCHO
APPEARED ON "AGT: THE
CHAMPIONS."
♪♪
>> WHEN I WALKED ONTO THAT
STAGE, EVERYBODY LOOKED AND EARP
THIS, LIKE, THAT'S HER?
BECAUSE I LOOK SO DIFFERENT FROM
WHEN I WAS 10.
>> BACK IN 2016, JACKIE FIRST
COMPETED ON "AGT" AS A LITTLE
GIRL.
NOW A TEEN, SHE'S ALL GROWN UP
AND LIVING IN HER OWN NEW YORK
APARTMENT.
>> THIS IS WHERE I REST MY
LITTLE HEAD.
>> HER NEW ALBUM "THE DEBUT"
COMES OUT THIS SPRING.
SHE MADE HEADLINES WHILE COMING
OUT ABOUT HER EATING DISORDER.
SHE CREDITS THERAPY.
>> THEY TEACH YOU SELF-LOVE A
>>> ON THE SET WITH
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
>>> I WORRY MYSELF SICK ABOUT
IT, AND THAT'S NOT GOOD FOR MY
HEALTH.
>> THAT IS WHAT ABBY LEE MILLER
TOLD ONLY "E.T." BACK IN APRIL
OF 2017 BEFORE SHE WENT TO
PRISON FOR BANKRUPTCY FRAUD, AND
IT'S SO EERIE TO HEAR THAT
BECAUSE SHE WAS DIAGNOSED WITH
CANCER.
NOW WE'RE SEEING JUST HOW HARD
ABBY HAS HAD TO FIGHT FOR HER
LIFE.
>> YOUR LIFE CHANGES COMPLETELY.
>> THESE ARE SHOCKING NEW IMAGES
OF THE "DANCE MOMS" STAR CRYING
IN HER HOSPITAL BED FIGHTING FOR
HER LIFE.
>> I WAS READY TO GO BACK TO
WORK AND START MY LIFE OVER, AND
NOW I CAN'T EVEN WALK.
>> SHE IS BATTLING A FORM OF
NON-HODGKIN'S LYMPHOMA, AND IN
THE NEW TRAILER FOR "DANCE MOMS
RESURRECTION," WE SEE HOW MUCH
OF A TOLL THIS IS TAKING.
>> I'M STARTING CHEMO.
>> THIS FOLLOWS THE BATTLE OF
TURBULENCE IN HER LIFE.
SHE PLEADED GUILTY TO BANKRUPTCY
FRAUD.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT TO FIGHT
ANYMORE.
YOU KNOW?
I HAVE, LIKE, THIS MUCH FIGHT IN
ME LEFT.
I DON'T WANT TO DEAL WITH IT.
>> IS THIS A FAIR PUNISHMENT
THOUGH IF YOU DO HAVE TO SPEND
TIME IN PRISON?
DO YOU THINK?
>> LIKE I TEACH MY KIDS, LIFE IS
NOT FAIR.
>> SHE SERVED SEVEN MONTHS IN
PRISON AND WAS RELEASED EARLY TO
A HALFWAY HOUSE.
WHILE SHE WAS THERE, SHE BEGAN
TREATMENT TO HER CANCER.
NOW AFTER LOSING HER HAIR TO
CHEMOTHERAPY, WE SEE HER DONNING
A WIG AND RETURNING TO TV, BUT
SOME THINGS NEVER CHANGE.
>> I NEED TO GET BACK TO
TEACHING AND TRAINING MY
CHILDREN.
I NEED TO GET BACK TO MY ROOTS.
I FOUGHT HARD TO BE HERE, AND
YOU HAVE TO BE A FIGHTER TOO.
>> SHE IS A FIGHTER.
WELL, "DANCE MOMS RESURRECTION"
WILL BEGIN AIRING IN JUNE ON
LIFETIME.
>>> STILL AHEAD TONIGHT --
♪ RAISE YOUR GLASS ♪
>> INSIDE PINK'S FAMILY
CELEBRATION.
WHY HER LITTLE GIRL IS THROWING
SHADE AT JUSTIN BIEBER?
PLUS, HER PERSONAL ADVICE FROM
THE SEXIEST MAN ALIVE.
>> WOULD YOU DO THAT?
>> OF COURSE.
I LOVE HIM.
>>> AND --
>> I'M ALWAYS, LIKE --
>> WITH SO MUCH TO WORRY ABOUT
BEFORE HER TALK SHOW DEBUT,
WHAT'S KELLY CLARKSON'S BIGGEST
FEAR OF ALL?
>>> CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED
BY --
♪♪
>>> DOLLY PARTON AND KATY PERRY
JOINED FORCES AT THE ACMs IN
2016, AND THEY WILL REUNITE AT
THE GRAMMYS AS WELL.
DOLLY, AN EIGHT-TIME GRAMMY
WINNER, AND MY FAVORITE, WILL BE
THE FOCUS OF A TRIBUTE FEATURING
KACEY MUSGRAVES, KATY PERRY AND
LITTLE BIG TOWN.
I CAN'T WAIT FOR THIS.
IT WILL BE A BIG NIGHT FOR PINK
SINCE "BEAUTIFUL TRAUMA" IS
NOMINATED FOR TOP ALBUM, AND SHE
WAS GIVEN HER OWN STAR ON THE
WALK OF FAME.
♪ SO RAISE YOUR GLASS IF YOU ARE
WRONG IN ALL THE RIGHT WAYS ♪
>> WHAT IS IT LIKE FOR THE KIDS
TO SIT ON YOUR STAR WITH YOU?
>> I THINK THEY'RE TERRIBLY
BORED AND THEY WANT TO GO HAVE
PIZZA.
>> OH, BUT WE WERE SO NOT BORED.
CHECK OUT THIS MOMMY MOMENT
BEFORE THE CEREMONY BEGAN.
2-YEAR-OLD JAMESON WAS IN TEARS
AND JUST WANTED TO BE WITH HIS
MAMA.
AS FOR WILLOW --
>> MY DAUGHTER WROTE ME A NOTE
AND IT SAYS, THIS IS A BIG DEAL.
I'M GLAD IT'S YOU AND NOT JUSTIN
BIEBER.
MY HUSBAND, HE'S SO CUTE.
HE'S MY MUSE, AND IF HE DIDN'T
PISS ME OFF ALL THE TIME, I
WOULD HAVE NOT MUCH TO SAY.
HE IS TOTALLY MY MUSE.
WE HAVE BEEN TOGETHER FOR 17
YEARS, AND IT IS WORK, BUT IT'S
WORTH IT.
>> PINK HAD HER ENTIRE FAMILY ON
HAND.
ELLEN CAME OUT TOO TO PAY
TRIBUTE.
>> SHY, LAZY, QUIET, TIMID, DOOR
MAT.
NO ONE HAS EVER USED THOSE WORDS
TO DESCRIBE YOU.
ONLY ME.
>> I FEEL LIKE THAT'S, YOU KNOW,
PARTLY TRUE.
I CAN BE SHY.
[ BLEEP ].
>> PINK RECORDED THIS LATE LAST
YEAR, AND JUST CHECK OUT THE
PRETTY EPIC HOOKUP WE MAY HAVE
JUST SCORED.
>> WELL, WE WERE JUST WITH HUGH
JACKMAN AND HE SAID --
>> IT WOULD BE A DREAM.
IF I HAD JUST ONE CONCERT AND
YOU WOULD COME AND SING WITH ME
ON STAGE AND BRING WILLOW TOO.
I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT
THAT.
♪♪
>> OF COURSE.
I LOVE HIM.
>> WELL, BEFORE THAT HAPPENS,
PINK WILL BE GOING HEAD TO HEAD
AGAINST KELLY CLARKSON AT THE
GRAMMYS.
BOTH ARE UP FOR VOCAL ALBUM.
KELLY'S NEW TALK SHOW LAUNCHES
THIS FALL.
SHE TELLS ELLEN TODAY WHAT HER
BIGGEST STRUGGLE IS.
>> I'M, LIKE, HOW DO I LISTEN?
MY NATIONAL INCLINATION IS
ALWAYS JOKE, JOKE, JOKE.
IT IS HARD FOR ME.
>> I HAVE A JOKE RIGHT AWAY, BUT
IF SOMEONE'S TALKING, I HAVE TO
LET THAT JOKE GO GOING, THAT WAS
A GOOD JOKE AND I JUST LET IT
GO.
>> OKAY.
I'M NOT A COMEDIAN, BUT I THINK
BECAUSE --
>> YOU CUT ME OFF JUST NOW.
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
>> SILENCE ISN'T OVERRATED.
I'M ALWAYS, LIKE --
>> THE 36-YEAR-OLD MOM OF TWO
HAS COME CLEAN WITH US ABOUT HER
OTHER BIG FEAR.
>> WHAT IF NOBODY SAYS YES?
WHAT IF NOBODY COMES TO MY SHOW?
YOU'RE ASKING PEOPLE TO TAKE THE
TIME ON SOMETHING THAT'S NOT
SUCCESSFUL YET.
HOPEFULLY MY FAMILY AND FRIENDS
WILL HELP ME OUT.
>> "E.T." HAS LEARNED KELLY'S
GUESTS INCLUDING CHRISSY METZ
AND JOSH GROBAN.
SHE WILL OPEN HER SHOW WITH A
SONG.
>> I FIGURED OUT IF I LED WITH
MUSIC, THEN IT MADE ME MORE
COMFORTABLE.
EACH SHOW, WE LEAD WITH MUSIC.
I COME DOWN SINGING JUST, LIKE,
A MINUTE OR WHATEVER.
>> THEY GET TO HEAR YOU SING TO
START?
>> IT'S NOT MY OWN STUFF.
I'M NOT -- THAT'S A LITTLE LAME,
BUT I GUESS IT'S VAIN TO BE
SINGING IN GENERAL, BUT
WHATEVER.
>> WE WANT TO HEAR YOU SING,
KELLY.
SING YOUR OWN STUFF AND TALK ALL
YOU WANT.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES HER ADORABLE.
YOU KNOW IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF
TIME BEFORE KELLY INTERVIEWS
ANYBODY FROM "THE BACHELOR," BUT
LAST NIGHT, BACHELOR NATION WAS
LEFT WITH A CLIFFHANGER AFTER
COLTON STORMED OFF AND SAID HE
WAS OVER IT.
CLEARLY TROUBLE IN PARADISE
THERE, BUT NOT ALWAYS THE CASE
FOR SOME OF OUR FAVORITE
BACHELOR COUPLES.
WE TEAMED UP WITH SECRETS
RESORTS AND SPAS FOR A WEEK OF
UNLIMITED LUXURY.
>> NOW THIS IS PARADISE.
>> GUYS, WELCOME TO SECRETS
CANCUN.
LET'S CHEERS.
HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE BACK IN
MEXICO WITHOUT THE DRAMA?
>> SO GOOD.
THIS IS OUR FIRST TIME IN MEXICO
SINCE WE GOT ENGAGED AND WE
DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT ANYONE
GETTING IN OUR WAY.
>> EXCUSE ME, GUYS.
>> LET'S START OFF WITH A WINE
TASTING.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> ARMANDO, HOW MANY DIFFERENT
WINES DO YOU HAVE IN THE CELLAR
HERE?
>> WE HAVE MORE THAN 400 LABELS
AND MORE THAN 2,000 BOTTLES.
>> CHEERS.
>> HAVING BEEN MARRIED, HAVING A
BEAUTIFUL BABY, WHAT KIND OF
WEDDED ADVICE ARE YOU GIVING
THESE TWO?
>> HAVE BABIES.
THEY'RE THE BEST.
>> WE'RE GOING TO WAIT UNTIL
AFTER THE WEDDING.
>> OKAY.
>> WHOA.
>> HEY.
>> VERY NICE.
>> WINE.
CHECK OUT THAT VIEW.
>> AH, THE BEDROOM, WHERE IT ALL
HAPPENS.
>> LOOK AT THE VIEW.
BABE, LOOK AT THE BATHTUB.
OKAY.
WE HAVE GOT TO CHECK THAT OUT.
>> WE NEED TO VACATION THERE.
IT'S AWESOME.
>> SOMETHING NEEDS TO HAPPEN
BECAUSE WHY AREN'T WE THERE?
>>> HEY.
WHEN WE COME BACK, WE'RE GETTING
READY FOR AMERICAN SOUL, AND A
FORMER DESTINY'S CHILD STAR IS
PLAYING GLADYS KNIGHT.
WHAT DOES SHE THINK ABOUT THAT?
YOU'LL HEAR WHAT SHE TOLD ME,
NEXT.
>>> TRAVEL CONSIDERATIONS
PROVIDED BY --
♪♪
>>> THAT IS KELLY ROWLAND
CHANNELING GLADYS KNIGHT IN THE
NEW TV SERIES "AMERICAN SOUL."
IT IS ALL ABOUT THE ICONIC '70s
DANCE SHOW "SOUL TRAIN," AND
KELLY NAILS IT.
>> IT HAS BEEN HONESTLY FROM THE
MOMENT I GOT DRESSED AND I
LOOKED AT MYSELF IN THE MIRROR,
AND I FELT LIKE, YOU KNOW, THAT
WAS, LIKE -- THAT'S THE BECOMING
GLADYS.
>> AND KELLY GOT THE STAMP OF
APPROVAL FROM THE EMPRESS OF
SOUL HERSELF.
>> YEAH.
THEY TELL ME KELLY WAS DOING IT.
I SAID, YAY!
SHE'S AMAZING.
MATTER OF FACT, SHE AND RANDY
WERE MY FIRST TWO CHOICES.
>> GOOD CHOICE.
>> THIS SERIES IS SO GOOD.
THE STORY BEHIND "SOUL TRAIN" IS
UNBELIEVABLE.
>> SHE LOOKS FANTASTIC IN IT.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE ONE MORE.
MICHELLE WILLIAMS IS PLAYING
DIANA ROSS.
THAT AIRS TONIGHT ON BET.
>> CANNOT WAIT TO SEE Y'ALL BACK
HERE TOMORROW.
"AMERICAN SOUL."
>> BYE, EVERYBODY.
>> BYE.
Your favorite restaurants now
deliver with DoorDash.
♪
It doesn't matter
where you are.
♪
It doesn't matter what
you're hungry for.
It doesn't even matter
how many you are.
♪
Restaurants come to you.
Delicious at your door.
Download DoorDash.
First order, no delivery fee.
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
>> ♪ Ready or not, here I come ♪
♪ You can't hide ♪