SUBJECTIVELY PEOPLE LOOK AT THE
PLAYER IN PARTICULAR.
THERE'S MANY THAT FEEL THE SAME
WAY.
I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
AND THE RHETORIC COMING OUT,
THEY DON'T FEEL THAT WAY.
THEY THINK HE HAD A FANTASTIC
YEAR.
TALKING ABOUT FUTURE PERFORMANCE
■■■■■■■■U#U#U#■#■#■■#■#?■#■#■■#
QUARTERBACK.
>> I AGREE WITH YOU.
IT'S SO IMPORTANT FROM AN
ORGANIZATION STANDPOINT YOU HAVE
TO PAY FOR FUTURE PERFORMANCE TO
HONOR THE PASS AND PAYU#U#U#■#■.
WE'LL GET TO THAT AS WE ROLL ON
HERE.
TOM BRADY'S CAREER HAD NO END IN
SIGHT.
AS HE AND THE PATRIOTS KEEP ON
WINNING SUPER BOWLS.
ARE THE PATRIOTS PLANNING ON
PAYING THEND HIS
SEASON?
♪ ♪
Plants capture CO2.
What if other kindCE&■■■■÷# t ■
If these industrial plants had
tech■=■=■=■=■;■;ç;■;■
that captured carbon like trees
we could help lower emissions.
Carbon Capture is important
technology -
and experts agree.
That's why we're working on ways
to improve it.
So plants...
can be a little more...
like plants.■■
♪ ♪
(Ariana)
What is he DOING?
(Vince)
He better not be messing up
our taxes.
(Lisa)
At H&R Block, you have your own
screen so you can see your
credits, deductions and tax
tips!
(Vince)
We need that now.
(Tax Pro)
What?
(Lisa VO) ♪
Know as you go at
H&R Block.
See your credits, deductions
and tax tips.
Block has your back.
♪ ♪
Creating the perfect night...
Just takes a little creativity.
The light beer you've been
waiting for has arrived.
Lower carbs.
Lower calories.
Higher expectations.
Corona Premier.
♪♪
Verizon got us VIP tickets
three feet away
from Justin Timberlake.
My Wife, me, JT.
(laughing)
What? Insanity.
(VO)
Get VIP tickets
to the best artists and more,
on us.
Plus, save big when you switch.
Only on Verizon.
Travel and dining
just go together.
Now KAYAK and OpenTable
let you earn travel rewards
every time you dine.
With just one reservation
on OpenTable,
you can start saving money
on hotels with KAYAK.
Get started at
KAYAK.com/diningrewards.
tx■■
(bird chirping)
Lots to do, hope you fuelled up.
Sure did.
That storm sure ripped through.
Yep, we gotta fix that fence
and herd the cattle back in.
Let's get at it.
(whistle)
(dog barking)
(♪♪)
[Soldier Chatter] Bandit three,
this is fox two three
can you see that contact
to our front?
Bandit, fox two three alpha,
we're marking 'em
with tracer fire.
There are those who choose
a different path in life.
[Soldier Chatter] Contact.
Contact front.
A path of selflessness...
of service.
A path that leads to freedom.
[Soldier Chatter]
Lay down suppressive fire!
DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES?
Find out at goarmy.com/warriors
>>> IN THE BATTLE VERSUS TIME --
EVERY YEAR ONE MAN■ ■ ■ ■ ■
FIGHT.
WHO CAN SURVIVE?
>> IF I DIDN'T KNOW HOW WOULD
BRADY  I WOULD SAY■28.
>> HIS INTERNAL FIRE■Xy■,y■<■■
>> SEASON AFTER SEASON.
GAMEER GAME.
THE QUESTION REMAINS, WILL THE
CLOCK EVER STRIKE MIDNIGHT Oa;
NUMBER 12?
>> THAT'S ON NFL LIVE AS WE
CONTINUE WITH BILL'S ONLINE
POST.
THE 11 NFL QUARTERBACKS WHO
COULD MEGAEXTENSIONS IN 2019.
AND HE CALLS GROUP THREE THE
HALL OF FAMERS, FOR GOOD REASON.
HE STARTS WITH■RADY.
$15 MILLION A YEAR.
WHAT A NEW DEAL COULD LOOK LIKE
THREE YEARS AND $45 MILLION.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I THINK I WAITED 20 YEARS FOR
■THE MOMENT.
I'VE WAITED MY WHOLE CAREER FOR
THE MENT.
BY THE WAY, WE'RE NOT TALKI■
ABOUT ANY DEADLINES HERE.
TOM BRADY IS THE EPITOME OF
FI■ CLA■■
HE'S GOING TO BE T WHEN THEY
NEED HIM.
■2U'RE NOT HEARING ANY OF THAT
NOISE COME OUGHT OF FOXBOROUGH.
IF H WANTS TO DO BY HIS
FELLOW QUARTERBACKS, TO ME, THE
THREE YEAR DEAL AT $90 MILLION
GUARANTEED, $30 MILLION A YEAR,
THAT'S WHAT THE FRANCHISE DATA
TAG IS.
HE'S GOING TO HELP HIS OTHER
QUARTERBACKS RESET THE BAR AND
SIGN A FULLY GUARANTEED CONTRACT
OF $90 MILLION.
>> IT'S INSANE TOM BRADY
NEVER MADE MORE THAN $19
MILLION.
HE'S INSANE.
A GUY WHO■■■7ñ/■>■;■;÷;÷;■@■;÷;.
IT'S INTERESTING ABOUT HIM ONE
YEAR LEFT ON HIS DEAL $23K
MILLION IN CASH.
THE TEAM RECENTLY DID SOME LEG
WORK TO PUSH THEM OUTTLE
BIT CLEARING $10LION THIS■y■=<■
SE
THEY WANT TO■■O THAT BUT
PROBLEM IS■YEAR'SARY
CAP SITUATION THEY'RE NOW
STARTING AT $20 MILLION WITH THE
CAP WHEN THEY DON'T HAVE DREW
BREES UNDER CONTRACT.
SO THAT'S A HUGE THING.
WHEN THEY TRY TO RESIGN
BREES, THEY'RE ALREADY GOING TO
BE DEALING WITH A MONSTER CAP
THAT I DON'T KNOW HOW IN THE
WORLD THEY GET IT DONE.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT DREW BREES
NEVER SKIMPS.
HE'S NOT A TOM BRADY.
HE WANTS THE MOST MONEY OUT OF
EV CONTRACT.
THIS, TO ■   C8 ■■ ■ GET STICKYT
BEFORE IT'S OVER.
>> NOW TO THE GROUP BILL TERMED
AS YOUNG GUNS.
START WITH CARSON WENTZ.
TWO YEARS NOW ABOUT $27 MILLION.
>> RIGHT.
AND CARSON WENTZ I WOULD BE
CONCERNED, OBVIOUSLY, HE MISSED
A NUMBER OF GAMES.■@
DURABILITY IS IS A CONCERN.
YES.
TWO YEARS AGO.
AND YOU HAVE TH FRANCHITA
OU NEE IT, THE YEAR AFTER.
TO ME IT WOULD BE STRU
STRUCTURE, AND STRUCT■
I WOULD TRY TO MINIMIZE THE
q■
I THINK $30 MILLION A YEAS■E■aQ
MATT RYAN IS WHICH IS WHAT HE'S
DONE FROM AN ON FIELD
STANDPOINT.
I'M GOING TO MAKE SURE THAT THE
GUARANTEED MONEY IS AS LITTLE AS
POSSIBLE AS THE FIRST TWO YEARS.
IF HE DOESN'T LIKE THAT, I'M
GOING TO LET HIM OFF THE
NEXT TWO YEARS AND THE FRANTIZE
TAG IN THE NEXT TWO YEARS.
>> HE WENT NUMBER TWO OVERALL.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THE
PROSPECTS FOR GOFF?
>> I LOVE WHAT IS GOING ON IN
L.A. AS FAR AS THE MARRIAGE
BETWEEN HIM AND SEAN McVAY.
THIS IS IS A GUY WHO BELIEVES IN
THE WAY THAT SEAN HAS CONNECTED
WITH HIM.
WHEN YOU LOCK AT OVEa THE PAST
TWO YEARS THE KIND OF C
RESURGENCE THEY'VE HAD.
HE'S TOP FIVE IN YARDS PER
ATTEMPT.
TOP TEN IN PASSER RATINGS.
AND, LOOK, I KNOW HE HAD A SUPER
BOWL WHERE IF HE MADE ONE MORE
THROW, REMEMBER THIS, ONE THROW
THAT MAYBE IS A YARD OR TWO
FURTHER, HE'S GOING TO BE 25
YEARS OLD IN SEPTEMBER.
HE HAS THE PERFECT SITUATION
GOING ON WITH THE HEAD COACH.
>> YEAH.
THING IS A GUY YOU LOCK UP FOR
SURE.
>> YEAH.
>> D NOT -- DON'T■÷■÷]÷ START T
BE TOO SMART.
THERE'S A LOT OF QUARTERBACKS
WHO WOULD HAVE LOOKED BAD IN
THAT SUPER BOWL.
LOCK THE KID UP.
CONTINUE TO BUILD THE FOOTBALL
TEAM.
CONTINUE TO MAKE SURE YOU TAKE
CARE OF THE DEFENSE.
ESPECIALLY ON THE EDGES.
LET THE KID CONTINUE TO DEVELOP.
YOU CAN HAVE YOUR FRANCHISE
QUARTERBACK FOR A LONG TIME.
>> FROM THE TIME HE STEPS ON THE
SUPER BOWL FIELD, HE'LL BE IN A
BETTER QUESTION.
>> NO QUESTION.
THERE'S A LOT OF TALK ABOUT THE
COWBOYS AND MAINLY DAK PRESCOTT.
>> I THINK JERRY JONES LOVES DAK
PRESCOTT MORE THAN ANY GENERAL
MANAGER IN THE NFL.
THAT'S GOOD FORdada? ? ? z8z8@/.
A BETTER COM PAG■@■SS INTERCEPT/
RUSHING TOUCHDOWNS.
ACROSS THE BOARD, STRANGELY
ENOUGH, WE ALL I THINK ARE PRONE
TO THINK THAT WILSON WOULD BE
PUTTING UP BIGGER NUMBERS THAN
PRESCOTT.
WELLSON WILL MAKE MORE MONEY
THAN PRESCOTT.
I THINK, THOUGH, PRESCOTT, WHEN
YOU TALK ABOUT FUTURE
PROJECTIONS IS YOUNGER THAN
RUSSELL WILSON.
I THINK HE'LL HAVE A CASE TO
MAKE OF WHY HE SHOULD MAKE
MONEY.
>> HE'S A REMARKABLE GUY.
YOU GO BACK AOU■ YEARS
AGO THE■■ DRAFT DAY AND
DISAPPOINTMENT OF PRESCOTT BEING
A FOURTH ROUND PICK.
HE'S IN A BETTER SITUATION■■■■■
DAK PRESCOTT IN THE BEST
POSITION OF THESE THREE
QUARTERBACKS.
>> GET YOURaR.
>>> COMING U ON NFL LIVE.J n n ■
■z//, MOST
POSITIONS THIS SEASON.
YOU MIGHT SEE BE SURPRISED TO
SEE WHO IS NUMBER ONE.
>>> AND WE CONTINUE OUR FIRST
ROUND FRIDAYS WHERE WE'LL TAKE A
LOOK BACK AT THE 2016 DRAFT
CLASS.
STICK AROUND.
■■■■■A■AA■@@■■■■AAA
♪ ♪
Give Extra. Get Extra.
There are thosd foady.
Ready to defend the nation.
Ready to fight for
what matters.
No matter what.
DOE WHAT IT TAKES?
Find out at goarmy.com/warriors
PLANNING AHEAD IS BROUGHT TO YOU
BY --
>>> BACK ON "NFL LIVE."
TODD ARCHER HAS NEWS ON DEMARCUS
LAWRENCE.
DESCRIBED BY STEPHEN JONES AS
BEING AT AN IMPASSE IN
NEGOTIATIONS.
THE TEAM AND THE AGENT FOR
LAWRENCE ARE TALKING AGAIN ABOUT
A LONG-TERM DEAL AND THERE'S
BEEN SOME BACK AND FORTH BUT THE
CONTRACT IS NOT YET CLOSE,
ACCORDING TO A SOURCE.
>>> IN THE MEANTIME, MONEY BEING
HANDED OUT LEFT AND RIGHT TO
DEFENSIVE GUYS THIS OFF SEASON.
THE LARGEST DEAL IN TERMS OF
GUARANTEED MONEY GIVEN OUT THIS
OFF SEASON WAS TREY FLOWERS WHO
SIGNED A FIVE-YEAR DEAL WORTH
$56 MILLION GUARANTEED.
FOUR OF THE TOP FIVE CONTRACTS
IN TERMS OF GUARANTEES HAVE GONE
TO DEFENSIVE PLAYERS WITH NICK
FOLES AS THE EXCEPTION.
ALL RIGHT.
AS THEY EXPLODE ON DEFENSIVE
TALENT.
TAKE US THROUGH WHO YOU THINK
WILL BE THE MOST IMPACTIVE.
START WITH FIVE AND WORK YOUR
WAY UP.
>> YEAH.
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT
DEFENSIVE IN FREE AGENCY.
I'M ABOUT FOLLOWING THE BREAD
CRUMB TRAIL.
MEANING RELATIONSHIPS.
AND THAT'S FOSTERS THE MOST
PRODUCTIVE SIGNING IN FREE
AGENCY.
WE'RE GOING TO START AT NUMBER
FIVE.
LET'S TAKE BRYCE■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■.
HIS ADMISSION TO THE■■S
HE CAME FROE CHICAGO BEARS.
WHO IS HIS NEW HEAD COACH IN
DENVER?
RIGHT NOW BIG BENOS WHAT BRYCE
CAN DO.
REMEMBER THIS GAME LAST YEAR.
THEY WON THE FOOTBALL GAME.
THEY WON IT BY ATTACKI■■■■
MIDDLE OF THE FIELD.
AND BRYCE CALLAHAN WASN'T ON THE
FIELD.
HE'S A NICKEL CORNER.
HE'S GOING T.7 INTEGRAL
PART OF THE BRONCO GOING
FORWARD.
THINK ABOUT THE AFC WEST AND HOW
THEY LIKE TO ATTACK.
BRYCE CALLAHAN WILL PLAY A MAJOR
ROLE IN HOW THE FOOTBALL TEAM
DOES GOING FORWARD.
NUMBER FOUR JUSTIN HOUSTON.
GOING FROM KANSAS CITY TO
INDIANAPOLIS.
WHO IS THE NEW GENERAL MANAGER
THERE?
CHRIS.
WHERE DID CHRIS COME FROM?
THE KANSAS CITY CHIEFS.
THEY NEED P RUSH.
ING ON THING JUSTIN BRINGS FROM
A NEGATIVE STANDPOINT IS, ONE,
HE'S 30 YEARS OLD.
TWO, DUR■
AVAILABI0 0■ ■WHEN HE'S ON T■ F,
THIS GUY IS AN ABSOLUTE TERROR.
HE'S ONE OF THE BEST NOT ONLY
OM QUARTERBACKS ON THE GROUND
BUT TAKING THE BALL AWAY FROM
THEM, AS WAS HIS COUNTER PART
WHO YOU SEE DOWN HERE.
I DIDN'T PUT HIM ON THE LIST.
I KNOW PEOPLE ARE A LITTLE UPSET
ABOUT THAT.
HERE.EXT GROUP I'M GOI■■
I PACKAGED■=
THE TWO SMITH BROTHERS.
GOING TO GREEN BAY.
WHAT THEY■÷ NEEDED.
THEY?Z8?■s■s NEED OUTSIDE■)■%■%E
OVER THE GUARD AND THE CENTER'1
AND PLAY■■ TWO POINT AND THREE
POINT.
IF YOU SEE THEM IN PERSON+  A F.
THEY'RE LONG RANGING DYNAMIC
PLAYERmymy PERFECTLY WITH W
THEY WANT TOO IN GREEN BAY.
>> YEAH.
AND BOTH OF THOSE GUYS YOU
MENTION THE VERSATILE TILL.
MIKE WILL MOVE THE FRONT SEVEN
PLAYERS AROUND.
THEY CAN DROP AND RUSH.
E TWO GOOD SIGNS FOR
GREEN BAY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
EARL THOMAS.
>> THERE'S A LOT OF GUYS LEFT ON
>> SUREpb ARE.
THEY'RE GREAT■LAYERS.
EARL THOMAS GOING HERE TO
BALTIMORE.
BALTIMORE LOSES A GUY LIKE SMITH
AND THEY HAVE -- WHO IS ALSO OUT
THE DOOR.■■■HE SECONDARY TO BE
VERYR%■ ■Az ■t>Bk(y■y■1H1 IMPC
■S1S1S1 LOOKT THEIR GUHEa>ILL HT
SECONDARIES IN THE NFL.
I BELIEVE EARL THOMAS IS■Q
OVER■ GggR LIKE ERIC WE
HEAD -- WETTLE.
>> WE SEE IT SOMETIMES TEAMS
WILL PLAY PLAYERS FOR WHAT THEY
DID AND NOT WHAT THEY'RE GOING
TO DO.
HE MISSED 22 GAMES TO GIVE HIM
$32 MILLION IN GUARANTEES.
HIS DURABILITY IS A CONCERN.
>> NO QUESTION ABOUT THIS.
NUMBER ONE, LOOK AT THESE GUYS.
>>xC29■■ YEAH.
THE HONEYR G KANSAS
CITY.
THEY'RE GIDDY OVER THE■ GUY.■■■.
HEI Y
HE CAN PLAY NICKEL AND DIME AND
HE CAN COVER TREMENDOUS BALL
SKILLS.
GREATÑ TACKLER.
THEY LOVE THE EFFECT T■■■aça?a■
HE'S GOING TOAVE ON THEc■C■■zG■z
DEFENSIVE BACK.
>> THEY MEET A FEW TIMES.
>> I'M RIGHT THERE.
>> A MAN -- BUT I BELIEVE SO FAR
NUMBER ONE.
THE CHIEFS GAME LAST YEAR AND
THE SECONDARY MEETS.
>> YEAH.
JUST LIKE THE FACT YOU LOVE
COLLINS.
>> YEAH.
WHAT IS NOTICEABLE BEFORE WE GET
TO EVERYBODY.
YOU LEFT OFF WHEN YOU LOOK AT
THE TOP GUYS.
JUST FROM THE LOCKER ROOM
STANDPOINT.
>> YEAH.
LEADERSHIP NOT ALL THE MOST
VOCAL GUYS.
BUT INCREDIBLE LOCKER ROOM
PRESENCE.
■=■■■■
>> TELY.
>> THAT'S WHAT THEY LOVE IN
PARTICULAR.
THEY CAN IMPACT ON THE REST■u■uí
THE GROUP.
>> THEY LOVE THAT.
>> SOMEONE
DEFENSIVE■; BACK FIELD.
I'LL TELL YOU WHY I LEFTIM■■ OF
■1■1■d■■
THE■4S THAT■ WORK OUT OR THE
GUYS YOU HAVE COMMONALITY WITH
THAT YOU'VE KNOWN IN THE sí
HANT TO PROVE.
THERE'S SOME KIND OF RH■p
DYNAMICS.
THEY HAVE A RELATIONSHIP OR
SOMETHING THAT LEAD YOU TO
BELIEVE WHEN THEY STAY ON THE
FIELD THEY'LL RETURN KIND OF
RETURN YOU NEED GIVEN WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO PAY.
>> YEAH.
WHAT IS A DB'S BEST FRIEND?
>> A PASS■■ RUSH.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
ABSOLUTELY.
HIM AND ALEXANDER YOU DRAFT NICK
BOSA.
IT'SXd GOING TO BE A POTENT
DEFENSE.
CHE CHANGE THE TEAM HIMSELF.
>> YEAH.
WHY DIDN'T YOU RESIGNHIM.
>> THERE'S SOME GREAT TALENT
HERE.
NOBODY IS WRONG.
>> YEAH.
>> THE BROWNS ANNOUNCE TWO
SIGNINGS TODAY.
PLAYING FOR THE ORLANDO AND THE
AAF.
A LITTLE FUN FACT THEY WENT TO
THE SAME HIGH SCHOOL AS BROWNS
STARTING QUARTER MAY 0v■g
FOUR YEARS0ú0p0úp0■p■púp■■■■÷■■z
>> AS WE CONTINUE, A FIRST ROUND
FRIDAY.
THIS WEEK WE DIVE INTO THE 2016
DRAFT CLASS.
OUR GUYS WILL TELL YOU WHICH
PLAYERS WERE BOOS AND NOT SO
MUCH.
I really didn't
expect to learn
so many interesting details.
AncestryDNA was
able to tell me
where my father's family
came from in Columbia.
They pinpointed the
Columbian and Ecuador region
and then there's a
whole new Andean region.
That was incredibly
exciting because
I really didn't
know that.
We never spoke
about that in my family.
It just brings
it home how deep
my roots are and it
connects me to them,
and to their spirit,
and to their history.
20 million members
have connected
to a deeper family story.
Order your kit at Ancestry.com.
■=i=to a deeper family story.
Guys do whatever it takes to
deal with shave irritation.
So, we re-imagined the razor
with the new Gillette SkinGuard.
It has a unique guard
between the blades.
That's designed to reduce
irritation during the shave.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
Gillette.
Emerge Restored,
Replenished,
Fortified.
Emerge everyday with Emergen-C.
Packed with B vitamins,
Electrolytes, Antioxidants,
Plus more vitamin C than
10 oranges.
Why not feel this good
every day?
Emerge and See.
-Omar, look.
[ Thunder rumbles ]
Omar, check this out.
Uh, yeah, I was calling to see
if you do laser hair removal.
For men.
Notice that my hips
are off the ground.
[ Engine revving ]
And then, I'm gonna pike
my hips back into downward dog.
[ Rhythmic tapping ]
Hey, the rain stopped.
-A bad day on the road
still beats a good one off it.
-Tell me about
that dental procedure again!
-I can still
taste it in my mouth!
Quit eating your burgers
off a coffee table.
If you want to eat a burger,
put it on a bar.
Follow your instincts to B-Dubs
for the new
All-American Cheeseburger.
Fresh, juicy beef smashed till
it's crispy around the edges,
covered in gooey cheese
and stacked to the ceiling
with deliciousness.
And knock that baby down with
a frosted beer at the bar,
just like the sports
gods intended.
The new
All-American Cheeseburger
at Buffalo Wild Wings.
Rooaaar!
I d with your
grandmother's doctor.
at Buffalo Wild Wings.
■■■■8
I d with your
grandmothHi.s doctor.
This is the man that's going
to check your eyes grandma.
Cognizant AI solutions
are helping healthcare companies
advance diagnostics
and prevent blindness
in patients with diabetes.
Everything looks good.
You have beautiful eyes.
♪
>>> GOOD EVENING.
WELCOME TO THE NFL ■8AFT. >> NO
>> IT'S NOT AN EARTHQUAKE IN NEW
YORK.
THAT'S JUST A VERY DISAPPOINTED
JET FAN.
>> WE HAVE A CHANCE.
YOU PASS ON HIM.
YOU HAVE TO BE KIDDING ME.
>> TO PASS UP TRENT.
FORGET IT.
>> WAY TO MINCE WORDS.
TRYING TO FIND JARED JONES.
>> OUR LEAD UP TO THE 2019 DRAFT
IS FAWN TO TAKE A LOOK IN THE
REAR VIEW MIRROR AND SEE HOW
THINGS STAND OUT.
WE CALL IT FIRST ROUND FRIDAY.
AND TODAY WE GO BACK TO 2016.
WHERE Y'ALL REMEMBER IT WAS ALL
ABOUT GOFF OR WEDNESDAY.
WEDNESDAY OR GOFF■ ■■■ ■■ GOING
OVERALL.
EVERYBODY HAD A CHOICE HERE WHO
THEY THINK ARE SOME OF THE BEST
PICKS OF THE FIRST ROUND.
AND THEN WE FOLLOW WITH NO SO
GREAT.
SO MEL IS BACK WITH US.
LET'S START WITH YOU.
WHO WOULD YOU SAY WAS THE BEST
PICK OF THE 2016?
>> SOME GUYS EMERGE AT DIFFERENT
TIMES IN THEIR CAREER.
HUGE HANDS.
HE WENT FOR THREE SACKS AND 12
SACKS ONE OF THE LEADING
TACKLERS.
BOWLER WAS INSIDE AND OUTSIDE
PRESSURE.
BUCKNER BECAME A BIG TIME PLAYER
THIS YEAR AND LIVED UP TO BEIÑI
>> I'M GOING WITH JOEY■.
I REMEMBER SITTING IN
COMBINE.OLIS WHEN HE RAN HIS■>:
WHEN HE'S ON THE QUARTERBACK
FIELD, HE PUTS QUARTERBACKS
DOWN.
THIS IS A SLAM DUNK PICK FOR
THEM.
IT SEEMS LIKE THERE WAS PEOPLE
TRYING TO OVER THINK THIS.
BUT HE'S A PASS RUSHER.
HE WAS READY TO GO WHEN HE CAME
OUT OF COLLEGE.
THE CHARGERS NAILED THAT PICK.
>>■@■@■@%@ YEAH.
>> WHAT PICK DID YOU LIKE?
>> EZEKIEL ELLIOT.
FOURTH PICK IN THE DRAFT.
OVER 4,000 RUSHING YARDS.
135 CATCHES.
HE NEVER COMES OFF THE FIELD.
YOU TALK ABOUTAK PRESCOTT,
QUARTERBACK IN THE RUNNING GAME,
HE CAN PASS PROTECT.
HE'S A PRO.
VERODUCTIVE.
BEST DAYS AHEAD OF HIM.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> ARGUABLY THE MOST INTERESTING
MOMENT I HISTORY OF THE NFL
DRAFT, WHICH MIKE WAS INVOLVED.
LAREMY TUNSIL.
THERE'S NO WAY HE SHOULD HAVE
OVERALL PICK.E IN THE 13th ■
HE DOWN THE DOLPH SAID
WAIT A SECOND.
OVER A GAS MASK?
OVER SOME MARIJUANA?
I DON'T WANT TO PUT WORDS IN
YOUR MOUTH.
>> AND HE DESERVES ALL THE
CREDIT IN THE WORLD.
WE'RE SITTING THERE AT THE
COMBINE AND 60 INTERVIEWS AND
TENNESSEE IS ON THE CLOCK.
EVERYONE IS CONVINCED TUNSIL IS
■  ONE.
COME ON.
WE HAVE TO MEET WITH THE GUY.
NEVER KNOW.
SURE ENOUGH, THE GAS MASK
HAPPENS AND A COUPLE OF TRADES
HAPPEN AND GOFF AND WEDNESDAY
GOES.
AND BALTIMORE AND THIS COULD
HAPPEN.
THE OWNER AND MYSELF WE LOOKED
AT EACH OTHER AND SAID THIS IS
AN UNBELIEVABLE OPPORTUNITY.
WE'RE ABOUT TO GET THE FIRST
PLAYER ON OUR BOARD AT 13;F
HE'S TURNED OUT TO BE A GREAT
PLAYER AND A GREAT PERSON.
>> WHERE'S THE GAS MASK?
>> I WAS IN THE GREEN ROOM WHEN
ALL OF THAT -- BY THE WAY,■ HIS
WHOLE TEAM3Eñ■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@@
HIS AGENT SAID■@■@■@■@■@■@EVER■@
GAIN ON SOC
A.
HO GET PREPARED FOR THE
DRAFT GOING INTO IT.
YEAH.L THE■rq■■■■t■EAD WAStttt■
■■■■■■■D ■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
IT WAS A REMARKABLE MOMENT.
>> THINGS WORKED OUT GREAT FOR
TUNSIL AND THE DOLPHINS.
>> WHICH PICKS HAVEN'T PANNED
OUT.
■   4 ,■■■■g■■g■■;■8 MINNESOTA
TREADWELL OUT OF OLE MISS.
HIGH HOPES.
HE■n■n■n HAS 56 CAREER RECEPTIO
ONE %HDYO4K/k■,
■á LATER, PICK 47,
MICHAEL THOMAS OUT OF OKLAHOMA
STATE HAS 23 TOUCHDOWNS.
TREADWELL IS 56.
RECEIVERS OVERALL HAVE BEEN
TOUGH TO EVALUATE.
A LOT OF DISAPPOINTING WIDE
RECEIVERS.
TREADWELL IS ONE OF THOSE.
>> YEAH.
GOING DOWN■uñE TO 26.
BUT QUARTERBACKJ POSITION■■mI■■R
HAS BEEN BEAN OF JOHN
ELWAY'S E■■O?í■OO<<■n■ @ ■
AND LYNCH NEVER SHOWE■■■b■■■■■7
OF SOMEONE BEING A
ANCHISEp QUARTERBACK.  MAKING■■.
I MEAN, IT DIDN'T WORK OUT FOR
THEM.
THEY HAVE CONTINUED TO CHURN AND
CHURN AND CHURN THAT POSITION.
RIGHT NOW WITH JOE FLACCO, THEY
DON'T HAVE THEVVV LONG-TERM ANS.
>> MIKE BELL?÷?÷Ñ■■) RECEIVER.
KOER I ARE COLEMAN WAS THE'ST■#
RECEIVER PICKo■s■s■s■g■gÑÑ■c TH;
HE'S BEEN WITH FOU■v■p■v TEAMS R
AND AS MELó, MENTIONED, ADD
MICHAEL THOMAS THERE WHO
EVENTUALLY WENT IN THE SECOND
ROUND.
HE'S BEEN THE BIGGEST
DISAPPOINTMENT.
THE FIRST OF 33 RECEIVERS THAT
WEREIPICKED.
>> GUYS TENTH OVERALL.
ELI AP■&■@
TRADE TO THE THE SAINTS.V
MAYBE THE FRESH START W<<<<EL■n)
THIS IS A GUY CALLED BY LANDON
COLLINS ONE OF THE
ECTED GUYS  THE GIANTS
LOCKER ROOM LAST YEAR.
A CANCER IN THIS LOCKERM.
THAT'S AS LOW AS IT GET■■)■4■4■
GUY.
WE'LL SEE IF HE CAN MAKE THE
MOST OUT OF IT.
AS FAR AS IT WAS CONCERNED WITH
THE GIANTS, IT WAS A BUM.
>> REMIND US ALL, INEXACT
SCIENCE.
HOWEVER, FRONT OFFICES DOING
THEIR WORK.
GEMS TAKING AFTER THE FIRST
ROUND IN 2016.
DAK PRESCOTT WON 32 GAMES SINCE
2016.
HE'S SECOND MOST BY A
QUARTERBACK BEHIND TOM BRADY AND
TYRIQ HILL WHO HAS BEEN A 50
YARD TOUCHDOWN WAITING TO
HAPPEN.
THANK YOU TO MEL.
MEL, WE'LL SEE YOU AGAIN NEXT
WEEK.
AS WE ROLL ON, THE JETS UNVEIL
THEIR NEW UNIFORMS FOR THE 2019
SEASON.
THUMBS UP OR THUMBS DOWN?
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT.
x#■■■■■■8■■A
♪ ♪
Plants capture CO2.
What if other kinds of■■■t too■
If these industrial plants had
technolo■=■=■=■;■=■;■
that captured carbon like trees
we could help lower emissions.
Carbon Capture is important
technology -
and experts agree.
That's why we're working on ways
to improve it.
So plants...
can be a little more...
like plants.
♪♪
♪ ♪
Really?
[horn honks]
Man this is what I feel like
when I wear regular shoes,
cramped and uncomfortable.
We can arrange a little upgrade.
Which is why I wear Skechers...
Wide Fit shoes.
They have extra room throughout.
They're like a luxury
ride for my feet.
Try Skechers
Wide Fit shoes.
I switched to MiraLAX
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives
forcefully stimulate
They're like a luxury
ride for my feet.
the nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX works with
the water in your
body to unblock your
system naturally.
And it doesn't cause
bloating,
cramping, gas,
or sudden urgency.
MiraLAX.
Look for the pink cap.
:=
Verizon got us VIP tickets
three feet away
from Justin Timberlake.
My Wife, me, JT.
(laughing)
What? Insanity.
(VO)
Get VIP tickets
to the best artists and more,
on us.
Plus, save big when you switch.
Only on Verizon.
ñ1ñ1■■ñ#■#■■■ ■#■@■■■A■A■■■
A fantastic marching band,
national champions, and a real
FREEBIRD!
See it here perform-
RD!n't think thuests.
PLEASE PLAY FREEBIRD
Every band knows it.
They're dying to play it.
Just OK is not OK.
Whether it's announcers  or
wireless networks.
AT&T is  America's best wireless
network,
according to America's biggest
test.
Now with 5G Ev■
the first step to 5G.
MORE FOR YOUR THING. THAT'S OUR
THING.
>>> EARLIER IN THE SHOW WE ASKED
YOU TO WEIGH IN ON THIS.
A NEW ERA FOR THE JETS UNVEILED
LAST NIGHT.
FIRST NEW UNIFORMS SINCE 1998.
>> IT FEELS LIKE IT'S A LOT OF
EXCITEMENT.
IF WE'RE NOT GOING TO HYPE IT,
THEN WHO IS?
WE KNOW IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
THERE.
RIGHT.
WE'RE GOING HAVE YOU GO FIRST.
THERE WAS A POLL.
I WAS WONDERING WHAT YOU GUYS
THINK.
SO SINCE YOU SPENT A NUMBER OF
YEARS THERE IN NEW YORK WITH THE
JETS, I'M WONDERING WHAT
PERCENTAGE OF THE VOTE WOULD YOU
GIVE?
>> NOT ONLY DO I KNOW THE
ORGANIZATION, I HAPPEN TO KNOW
THE HEAD COACH PRETTY WELL.
ON A PERCENTAGE BASIS, MY
PERCENTAGE WOULD BE 0.
THE QUESTION IS WHO ARE THE
CHANCES OF ADAM GASE BEING THERE
OR WATCHING IT?
I PROMISE HE WAS WATCHING SAM
DARNOLD.
>> NOT TOO SHABBY.
>> WE'LL TRY IT AGAIN.
>> LOOK AT THE SMYLY FACE.
>> HERE.
KNOW WHAT?
>> YEAH.
WE DON'T WANT TO HIT IT.
■÷■h■■@■GO.
>> YEAH.
>> I DID IT.
OKAY.
YEAH, WE DO THAT.
WE TURN IT BACK UP.
>> HUH.
>> I WOULD PROBABLY DO THE SAME
THING.
IT'S NOT SHOO SHABBY.
THE LAST THING I CARE ABOUT WITH
THE JETS ARE THEIR UNIFORMS.
I CARE ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT THEY
CAN PROTECT THEIR QUARTERBACK.
DEVELOP THEIR QUARTERBACK.
I'M PRONE HAVING MAN CRUSHES ON
CERTAIN GUYS.
HE'S ONE OF THOSE.
>> YEAH I'M THE WORST WHEN IT
COMES TO UNIFORMS.
I DON'T CARE.
THEY LOOK A LITTLE BIT
COLLEGIATE.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> I KNOW I WAS UPBEAT.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I'M BIG ON UNIFORMS BUT I
KNOW A LOT OF PEOPLE FEEL LIKE I
DO.
THEY GO WITH THE THROW BACK.
THE HEYDAY AND THE JOE NAYMUTH.
>> WHEN THE DOLPHINS ROLL OUT
THEIR THROW BACKS, PEOPLE GO
CRAZY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I WISH THEY HAD GONE WITH MORE
OF A THROWBACK.
>> IT'S HARD TO GET THAT ON MY
PHONE, TOO.
>> WHAT IS GOING ON WITH MY HAIR
THERE THE FRIDAY STAPLE.
WE HAVE A ROOKIE TODAY AND IT
SHOULD BE FUN.
COUNTING FLAGS.
CHALLENGE FLAGS WILL HAVE TO DO
WITH THE NEW HEAD■7 COACHES
OPENING WORK OUTS FOR NEXT WEEK.
WE'VE GOT CHALLENGES.
♪ ♪
Give Extra. Get Extra.
There are those who see the
challenges facing
the nation and say send me.
They fight for country.
They fight for honor.o
They fight to win.
DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES?■
Find out at goarmy.com/warriors
From the start, the C-Class
was ahead of its time.■
Still,w>■>■>■>d
making it stronger.
Faster.0@7■■■⌞■⌞■■■
Smarter.
Because to be the best,
is to never ever stop
making it better.
The 2019 C-Class Family.■
Visit your local Mercedes-Benz
dealer for exceptional
lease & financing offers
during the Mercedes-Benz
Spring Event.
Going on now.
■0>ú/■=
♪
Lift away itch, flakes, and
doubt.
Stay Headstrong with Head &
Shoulders
CLASSIC SURRENDER COBRA.
GOOD THING I ORDERED WENDY'S.
I'VE GOT A DELICIOUS
S'AWESOME BACON CHEESEBURGER,
A BARBECUE CHEESEBURGER
AND A PEPPERCORN MUSHROOM.
DOWNLOAD OUR APP NOW
AND GET WENDY'S MADE TO CRAVE
CHEESEBURGERS DELIVERED.
With Advil, you'll ask...
What sore muscles? What
pounding head?
Ad... Relief that's
fast. Strength that lasts.
You'll ask...
Ad... Relief that's
fast. StrWhat pain? lasts.
With Advil.
SPORTS CENTER 6:00 P.M. EASTERN.
THE COLLEGE GAME DAY CREW JOINS
THE SHOW TO PICK THE FINAL FOUR
WINNERS.
PLUS, WHAT IS REALLY WRONG WITH
THE 2-6 RED SOX.
AND MORE FROM THE DWAYNE WADE
CONVERSATION AS HE WRAPS UP HIS
FAREWELL TOUR.
"SPORTS CENTER" ON ESPN AND THE
ESPN APP.
NOW FOUR NEW HEAD COACHES
STARTED THEIR OFF SEASON THIS
WEEK.
FIVE■g;g■2■2E EIGHT PLAID
QUARTERBACK IN COLLEGE.
CARD CLIFF■S BURY.wk@■■■■R■■@■@1
REMEMBER HIM AT TEXAS TECH.
HE HELD 39CHOOL■■ ■ ■ RECORDS,
NCAA■■ RECORDS.C■■
NOT TOO BAD.
>> YEAH.
>> ON WE GO.
OLD SCHOOL BUCCANEERS.
BRUCE ARIANS.
HE WAS THE STARTER IN 1974.
>> I WAS FIVE.
I LIKE THIS VIDEO.
YOU CAN SEE HIM PUT IT ON HISúú
LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S BALL HANDLING THERE.
>> SO B.A.
>> YEAH.
FR■@>7@■ñj■8■>OACH
OF THE BROWNS.
>> LOOK AT THAT. ■> YEAH.
HE WENT 22-13 AND PLAYED IN
THREE BOWL GAMES.
>> WE SAW QUARTERBACK GO UNDER
CENTER IN COLLEGE.
>> YEAH.
>> PUT A 34 NUMBER ON HIM AND HE
WOULD BE A NICE FULL BACK.
>> YEAH.
AND ZACK TAYLOR WITH THE BACK UP
AT WAK FOREST AND TRANSFERRED
TO KANSAS LEADING THEM■p
FINAL CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
THEN HE WAS A TWO YEAR STARTER
A A ■ ■ ■ ■
>>
GO BIG RED.
THAT'S A BIG ■ ■THE WAY.
>> YEAH.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN A LOT OF ADAM
GAS.
>> YEAH.
SAGINAW VALLEY STATE IN 2002.
REACHED THE PLAYOFFS.
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT KYLER
MURRAY NOT BUILT TO LAST.
HAVING THE NICKEL CORNER.
NOT CERTAINLY THAT ONE OF A
QUARTERBACK.
>> SAGINAW VALLEY.
>> I LOVE.
WILL NOT SEE ADAM GASE.
>> NO.
>> NOT■■■@■■■■ó■■ó■#N=N=■■■■■■■H
NICK SABAN.
>> THE FOUR TEAMS■=Nu■%ó■■■ó■■■
WEEK ARE THE SUBJECT OF OUR
>> YEAH.S.
GREEN BAY PACKERS.
THIS IS OBVIOUS NOW.
AARON ROGERS THIS CHALLENGE IS
FOR YOU, MAN.
PROTECT YOUR LEGACY.
PROTECT YOUR REPUTATION.
STAND UP.
BE A LEADER.
LIVE THE PEOPLE AROUND YOU.
YOU'RE ONE OF THE GREATEST
YERS.
LA THIS GAME EVER.
PROTECT YOURSELF.
>> THE FLAG FOR LE'VEON BELL.
ON MONDAY YOU'LL GET HIGH OCTANE
OFFENSING.
YOU'LL GET COACHED ON OFFENSE
LIKE YOU NEVER HAVE BEEN BEFORE.
THERE'S A LOT OF EXPECTATIONS T
CLIFF AND STEVE KEIM.
THIS IS A TEAM RIGHT NOW THAT
ULTIMATELY HAS TO DECIDE BIG
TIME ON KYLER MURRAY■8 OROSH
ROSE.%%%■■■E THE M