2017 NIGHTMARE, IN IS THIS PAST
WEEKEND.
THAT'S HIM BOX JUMPING WITH JUST
A LITTLE HELP.
QUOTE SOMEONE FROM HIS
ORGANIZATION FROM MANY YEARS
AGO.
DON'T GIVE UP, DON'T EVER GIVE
UP.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
KEVIN: FANTASTIC.
GOOD LUCK TO THE BETTOR WHO
DROPPED $1500 IN NOVEMBER ON
TEXAS TECH TO WIN IT ALL.
200-1 ODDS, IF THAT HAPPENS
TONIGHT, $300K IN THE BAG.
KEITH: IT WAS ME.
[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BYING.
ESPN, INC.]
>> BASEBALL TONIGHT FROM THE
LONE STAR STATE FROM GORGEOUS
MINUTE MAID PARK.
FANS WILL BE TREATED TO A REALLY
GOOD MATCHUP BETWEEN THE ASTROS
AND THE NEW YORK YANKEES.
WELCOME TO MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL
ON ESPN!■■■
ASTROS AND YANKS HERE TONIGHT
AND OUR TELECAST IS PRESENTED BY
USAA.
♪[MUSIC]♪♪
>> IT'S A BANGED UP YANKEE TEAM.
AARON JUDGE IS HEALTHY, HOWEVER,
AND READY TO GO.
YANKEES ON THE ROAD.
THEY'LL BE GOING UP AGAINST ONE
OF THE BEST YOUNG PLAYERS IN THE
SPORT IN ALEX BREGMAN.
A LOT OF TALENT ON THE FIELD
HERE TONIGHT, TWO OF THE BEST IN
THE AMERICAN LEAGUE.
WELCOME INTO THE BROADCAST
BOOTH.
JON SCIAMBI AND DAVID ROSS.
WE ARE TREATED TO A GREAT
PITCHING MATCHUP.
WE'LL GET TO MASAHIRO TANAKA IN
JUST A MOMENT.
BUT START WITH JUSTIN VERLANDER.
36 YEARS OLD.
SECOND IN THE CY YOUNG AWARD
VOTING LAST YEAR.
A POWER GUY.
IT'S INCREDIBLE, THE IMPACT HE'S
HAD SINCE COMING TO HOUSTON.
>> YEAH.
THIS GUY IS AN ABSOLUTE STUD.
HE'S ON A SHORT LIST FOR ME OF
NUMBER ONES IN THE GAME RIGHT
NOW.
HE'LL GO THROUGH THE LINEUP FOR
THE THIRD TIME, WHICH WE NEVER
SEE ANYMORE.
HE'S GOT A FOUR-PITCH MIX.
HE STUDIES AS HARD AS ANYBODY.
AND HE'S A RARE GUY THAT CAN
STILL READ SWINGS.
ON THE OTHER SIDE, IN TANAKA,
YOU'VE GOT A GUY THAT LIKES TO
GET THE HITTER TO EXPAND.
HE'S GONNA MAKE YOU HIT HIS
PITCH.
HE'S GOT A CUTTER AND A SLIDER.
HE'S GOT A DEVASTATING SPLIT
HE'LL THROW OFF THAT FASTBALL.
IF YOU'RE THE ASTROS, YOU GOTTA
GET HIM UP IN THE ZONE, SEE THAT
BALL UP.
IF YOU'RE CHASING DOWN, IT'S
GONNA BE OVER.
>> THE THEME FOR TANAKA IS THAT
HE DOES NOT GIVE IN.
FOR THE YANKEES, THEY HAVEN'T
GIVEN IN DESPITE ALL OF THESE
INJURIES IN THE EARLY GOING.
SEVERINO IS ON THE DISABLED
LIST.
SABATHIA, ANDUJAR.
NO GREGORY.
STANTON AS WELL.
BUT THEY'VE HAD OTHER GUYS PICK
IT UP.
I KNOW YOU LIKE FOCUSING ON THE
CATCHER, SO WE'LL TALK ABOUT THE
CATCHER, GARY SANCHEZ.
>> GOTTA GIVE THE CATCHER SOME
LOVE.
GARY SANCHEZ RIGHT NOW, THREE
HOMERS YESTERDAY, SIX R.B.I.'S.
HE IS LEADING MAJOR LEAGUE
SEBALL, TIED WITH CODY
g■■#■#R IN HOM
THIS GUY, WHATEVER YOU WANT TOS-
■
ç
>> ALL RIGHT.
BOOG, THANKS SO MUCH.
FUN MATCHUP IN HOUSTON PED
TONIGHT, POSSIBLE ALCS PREVIEW.
A COUPLE OF GAMES ON THE
SCHEDULE THIS■
EID IN■=HICAGO.
T THE RAYS AND THE WHITE
SOX?
BLAKE SMELL.
THAT SEASON OPENER,
NOTWITHSTANDING.
HE HAS BEEN GREAT.
HE WAS REALLYOOD AGAIN TODAY.
SIXTH INNING, JUST ONE EARNED
RUN.
11 STRIKEOUTS.
66 OF HIS 100 PITCHES WENT FOR
STRIKES.
HOW ABOUT THE RAYS NOW?
8-3 ON THE SEASON, BEST START
SINCE THE 2010 SEASON.
TAMPA TAKES CARE OF THE WHITE
SOX.
THEY WIN IT BY A FINAL OF 5-1.
MEANTIME, 2019 HOME OPENER AT
WRIGLEY FOR THE CUBS.
CHICAGO OFF TO A BRUTAL 2-7
START.
BUT THEY BROKE OUT TODAY.
MAYBE IT WAS THE OLD■■LE.
BEN ZOBRIST, TWO-RUN SIN
PLUS,TER WHO SCORED,
CAME UPY, WHILE HE WAS
WARMING UP, GRABBED THAT
HAMSTRING.
LEFT THE GAME IN THE THIRD.
M.R.I. THUNDERSTORM.
THEN REALLY SCARY MOMENT.■■
ANTHONY RIZZO LINES IT.
JAMESON TAILLON TAKES IT IN THE
DOME.
102 MILES PER HOUR OFF THE
FO■DID STAY IN THE GAME BUT NOT
MEANTIME, WE'RE KEEPING OUR EYE.
HOME TO THE NATS.
THREE HITS IN THE OPENER,
INCLUDING THAT MAMMOTH 458-FOOT
HOME RUN.
MEANTIME, MIKE TROUT AND THE
ANGELS, THE MAJOR LEAGUE-LEADING
BREWERS.
FIVE HOME RUNS.
WITH A HOME RUN TONIGHT, TROUT
WOULD MATCH BOBBY BONDS IN 1977
FOR THE L■ANGE51■1■á HISTORY.
AND CHRIS DAVIS IS IN THE LINEUP
TONIGHT.
BATTING SIX FOROLES.
INAUSPICIOUS START
CONTINUES.
TWO SHY OF THE MAJOR LEAGUE
RECORD OF CONSECUTIVE HITLESS
AT-BATS BY A POSITION PLAYER.
SO BRYCE AND THE PHILLIES HOME.
THE NATIONAL LEAGUE LEADING
DODGERS AND BREWERS BOTH IN
ACTION.
MAJOR LEAGUE LEADING MARINERS IN
ACTION AS WELL.
BRYCE AND THE PHILLIES, YOU CAN
SEE ON ESPN+.??7 7 ■ 7
WE'VE GOT A FABULOUS MATCHUP IN
STORE.
YANKEES AND ASTROS.
TANAKA AND VERLANDER.
BOOG AND ROSSI ON THE CALL.
COMING UP.
My experience with USAA
has been excellent.
They really appreciate
the military family
and it really shows.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
It was funny because
when we would call
■uld say
“Oh we can't beat USAA”
We're the Webber family.
We're the Tenney's
We're the Hayles,
and we're USAA members for life.
♪
Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
GATORADE ZERO.
ALL THE ELECTROLYTES.
ZERO SUGAR.
♪♪
♪♪■■■■i■■■:■:■■■■
GET MORE OUT OF ZERO.
■■■■■■■
Ñ■■■
>>>>>■>■>MY LAWN.
IT'S BEEN WORN DOWN
TO UGLY THIN GRASS!
■3
NOW THERE'S SCOTTS THICK'R
WITH A SOIL IMPROVER
TO STRENGTHEN ROOTS!
THE REVOLUTIONARY 3-IN-1
SOLUñ WEA
SEED TO FILL IN GAPS!
■    TO FERTILIZERED
A 50% THICKER LAWN
AFTER JUST ONE APPLICATION.
♪ ♪ ♪
■
NOW YARD TIME IS OUR TIME.
THIS IS A SCOTTS YARD.
>> ESPN'S TELECAST OF MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL IS PRESENTED BY
USAA.
INSURANCE, BANKING AND
INVESTMENTS TAILORED FOR THE
MILITARY COMMUNITY.
BACK HERE AT MINUTE MAID PARK,
AARON BOONE CHECKING IN AS THE
YANKEES SKIPPER.
ONE OF THE THINGS HE'S DEALING
WITH RIGHT NOW, A LOT OF
INJURIES, AS THE YANKEES HAVE A
WHOLE SLEW OF GUYS ON THE
DISABLED LIST.
ON THE INFIELD, DIDI GREGORIUS
WILL BE OUT A WHILE, FOLLOWING
TOMMY JOHN SURGERY.
TULOWITZKI JUST WENT ON WITH THE
BAD CALF.
STANTON OUT WITH THE BICEPS.
HICKS, HOPEFULLY BY THE END OF
THE MONTH.
ELLSBURY OUT AS WELL.
AND THEY'RE MISSING SEVERINO,
SABATHIA AND AS WELL, DELLIN
BETANCES.
SO AOT FOR THE YANKEES TO DEAL
WITH.
AND YET THEY'RE STILL SCORING.
IN FACT, THEY'RE SECOND IN THE
LEAGUE IN RUNS PER GAME.
HERE'S THE LINEUP THAT HE'S PUT
TOGETHER, WITH GARDNER, JUDGE
AND VOIT.
GLEYBER TORRES BEARS WATCHING.
HE'S BEEN HOT WITH THREE HOMERS
IN THE LAST THREE GAMES.
SEVEN HITS OVER THAT STRETCH.
THAT YANKEE LINEUP THAT'S RAKING
IN THE EARLY GOING WILL GO UP,
AS YOU MENTIONED, DAVID ROSS,
ONE OF THE TRUE ACES IN THE
GAME, JUSTIN VERLANDER.
GETTING THE START HERE TONIGHT.
>> YEAH.
COMING OFF A ROUGH START HIS
LAST TIME OUT.
THIS IS A GUY THAT HAS BEEN
REALLY TRYING TO EVEN CONTINUE
TO EVOLVE.
MIXING THE CHANGE-UP A LOT MORE.
STILL GOT THE FASTBALL AT 95, 96
MILES AN HOUR.
HE'S GOT THAT BIG BREAKING BALL
THAT WAS HIS STAPLE EARLY ON AND
A NASTY SLIDER.
HE'S GOT REALLY GOOD NUMBERS
AGAINST THIS YANKEE TEAM.
JON: JUSTIN VERLANDER WAS
G FOR A.J. HINCH, WORLD
CHAMPION A COUPLE OF SEASONS
AGO.
AND NOW THE EXPERIENCE THAT HE
HAD IN ARIZONA.
HE JOKINGLY WAS TELLING US,
PRIOR TO THE GAME, THAT THE
PLAYERS, BY AND LARGE, DO NOT
x PLAYING WITH THE ROOF OPEN.
THE FUNNY THING IS THAT -- AND
TODAY HERE IN HOUSTON, IT'S
SPECTACULAR.
I MEAN, YOU WOULD TAKE PLAYING
TODAY THAN EVERY MAJOR LEAGUE
CITY.
HERE'S THE HOOK.
WHEN YOU PLAY IN NEUTRAL
CONDITIONS AND YOU'RE USED TO
ROOM TEMPERATURE ALL THE TIME,
THEY OPEN THE ROOF AND THE
PITCHERS COMPLAIN.
AND THEY OPEN THE ROOF AND THE
HITTERS COMPLAIN.
AND THEY'RE GOING, HEY, ONE OF
YOU GUYS ARE WRONG, OK?
IT'S HARD TO HIT AND IT'S HARD
■mIT
>> YOU G THESE CONTROLLED
ENVIRONMENTS AND GET■ REALLY
SPOILED AS A PLAYER.
SOME GUYS LIKE IT OPEN, SOME
LIKE IT CLOSED.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MAKE ALL 25
GUYS HAPPY.
I'M GONNA GO TO MY SUPERSTAR AND
GO, HEY, BUDDY, WHAT DO YOU WANT
US TO DO?
JON: THERE IT IS, THE
VI■■o■JOY■■ BALLPARK.#■&■■■■■■■W
DOw■ RAIN DELAY, NO CHANCE OF A
■OO
YOU'RE STARTING ON TIME WITH A
BEAUTIFUL DAY, EITHER WAY.
JON: THE VETERAN, BRETT GARDNER.
YOU SEE THE SHIFTED■■c>o■■■OOO .
BREGMAN.
GARDNER WILL STILL BUNT.
VERLANDY TO ROCK AND
AWAY WE GO.
HEATER RIGHT THROUGH.
DAVID RACKLEY IS OUR PLATE
UMPIRE.
YOU SEE THE NUMBERS ON GARDNER.
WITH HICKS OUT,■8óu IN
oo■OG■G FIELD.
81■■■■go■■ D■■■E■■■■o■oTART THIS
k■■■O/8O■OO■■8■OOO■■Oo■O■■■oO■■■
FOç■■■ç■■■w■ IHE
CURVEB AND T SLIDER MIX
THAT HE WILLñ■U.
AND■■A■G ON THEAME, HE'LL
THROW MORE OF ONE OR MOREWW■■■[E
■■■OO■■■O=>4■4
DAVID: EVERY QUADRANT, HE'S
GOING TO USE TODAY.
JON: UP IN THE AIR, RIGHT FIELD,
REDDICK.
SLOWING DOWN, WITH THE
SUNGLASSES ON, HE MAKES THE
GRAB.
ONE AWAY.
HERE COMES AARON JUDGE.
GETTING STARTED HERE IN HOUSTON,
JON SCIAMBI, DAVID ROSS.
A COUPLE OF HOMERS THIS YEAR.
LAST YEAR, HIS SEASON CUT SHORT,
OR AT LEASTED, GUESS ■■  ■■■■■■E
INTO THE PLAYOFFS.YEAR
BUT THE 112 GAMES, BECAUSE OF
THAT RIGHT WRIST FRACTURE.
THIS GUY'S A CAR.
DAVID: HE'S A SUPERSTAR.
THIS GUY IS A STUD.
TWO-HOLE HITTER IN THE
I MEAN, WHEN I WAS COMING OUT, I
SAW THE TWO -- THE TWO-HOLE BE -
THIS IS■7■7■■/■/
YOU GOT YOUR BEST HITTER, YOUR
BEST■■■■■■[ ■■■■■■[■ HOLE.
YOU WANT■Q T■ A
LO
JON: LINED TO LEFT FIELD.
AND THAT'S A BASE HIT.
AND FOR AARON JUDGE, THAT IS HIS
FIRST CAREER HIT AGAINST JUSTIN
VERLANDER, INCLUDING THE
POSTSEASON.
HE HAD NEVER COME UP WITH A HIT.
AGAINST JUSTIN VERLANDER.
DAVID: HE MIGHT ASK FOR THE BALL
HERE.
0-13, AS YOU SAID, WITH SEVEN
K'S.
HITS THIS ONE OFF THE END HERE.
AMAZING TO      BIG AND STRONG
HE IS./■O■E BALL OFF THE END OFE
BAT AND ALMOST GO TO THE WARNING
TRACK.GGG■/S■O■;O@@Y@@3■■■@9@■Pá
HE'LL BE SIGNING THAT BALL
AFTERWARDS.
>> HE HAD BEEN 0-13 WITH SEVEN
STRIKEOUTS.
ANY PITCHER THAT H GOT AT-BATS
AGAINST, THAT WAS HIS LONGEST
0-FOR.
SO JUDGE WITH H.Ñs■■■/ KNOCK
T TH
■÷■÷m÷]h■÷m÷ ASTROS' ACE.■
AND HERE IS LUKE VOIT.
DAVID: LUKE VOIT H THAT
SECOND BUTTON TONIGHT.
JON: HA HA!
DAVID: NOT SURE WHY HE'S DOING
THAT.
BREAK OUT THE SWAG, LUKE!
I KNOW T/@ SHIRT
UNDERNEATH THERE.
JON: IF HE DOES, HE'S GOT IT
BUTTONED UP TO THE TOP.
DAVID: WHAT IS HE■nw÷w÷w÷w÷■÷S÷?
JON: AARON BOONE IN THE PLAYOFFY
HARD.
HE JOKINGLY COMPARED HIM TO JACK
HARTMAN FROM MAJOR LEAGUE TWO.
HA HA!
THRFECT.
FOULED IT OFF HIS FOOT.
SPLIT SCREEN.
YOU DECIDE.
UH-HUH.
YEAH.
DAVID: HE JUST NEEDS THE NO
EARFLAP.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU CAN WEAR
THAT ANYMORE.
JON: I DON'T BELIEVE YOU CAN.
BUT ON A SERIOUS NOTE, LUKE VOIT
CAME OVER LAST YEAR.
THE 29TH OF JULY.
THE ANALYTICS DEPARTMENT HAD
THOUGHT WOUi2i2i2 REALLY
PR WHEN■V■V@ LOOKED AT
HIM.
HIT RATE, WHEN THEY LOOKED AT
THE SLUG.
AND HE CAME OVER AND HE SLUGGED.
AGAIN, YOU'RGHE CAMEER ONHE 29TE
CARDINALS.ÑÑ#■■<b■OK AT ■;■; AUT
FREQU■C■/■) OF HOMER RATE■
AT-BAT.■
9.4 AT-BATS PER EVERY HOMER TO
THE END OF THE SEASON.
THAT LED THE MAJORS.
DAVID: WOW.
THAT'S WHY YOU SEE HIM IN THE
THREE HOLE TONIGHT■■■ H
THE NE■0KE VOIT■ú■■ú■■■■■■■■■■■D
THERE., THAT■■ú■■ú■■■8■ú■ú■■■■■@
HOW Mr&■4r&ñ>■&r&■&r&■?&r&■#
ANDE'S AT IN HIS CAREER,
NG OFF■■HAT YEAR HE HA
YEAR.
THIS GUY CAN PUT IT OUT OF THE
PARK AS GOOD AS ANYBODY.
AND YOU LOOK AT HIM -- THAT'S
WHY I WAS AMAZED AT BATTING
PRAC
I THINK THE YANKEES HAVE TO BE
THE LARGEST TEAM IN ALL OF
BASEBALL.
JUST BIG HUMAN BEINGS WALKING
AROU THERE.
JON: AND THERE'S■,■■
RIGHT.■NO.■>
JON: I GOT TO DO AN INTERVIEW
WITH STANTON WHEN HE WAS IN
MIAMI THE YEAR BEFORE LAST, WHEN
THE ALL-STAR GAME WAS IN MIAMI.
AND JUST OFF THE AIR, SAYING TO
HIM, GEE, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HE'S A LOT BIGGER THAN YOU.
YOU'RE USED TO BEING BIGGER THAN
EVERYBODY ON THE FIELD.
AND JUDGE IS EVEN BIGGER THAN
YOU.
AND HE JUST SMILED.
HE'S LIKE, I CAN'T WAIT TO MEET
HIM.
AND NOW THEY'RE TEAMMATES.■■
JUST GETTING GOING HERE IN
N.
THE ROOF IS OPEN.
CROWD STILL FILING IN.
EARLY SEASON MATCHUPETWEEN TWO
TEAMS TO BE SOME  THE1■ THE AME.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT FOR YOU, BUT
I WOULD HAVE A HARD TIME
IMAGINING THAT IF WE'RE SITTING
HERE IN SEPTEMBER, THAT WE'RE
NOT STILL TALKING ABOUT THE
ASTROS AND YANKEES AS TWO OF THE
BEST IN THIS LEAGUE.
DAVID: NO DOUBT.
YOU LOOK AT, EVEN WITH THE
YANKEES BANGED UP, THE DEPTH OF
THAT LINEUP THEY STILL HAVE, AND
ALL THE HOME RUNS THEY'VE
ALREADY HIT, IT'S BEEN REALLY
ONE OF THESE THINGS THAT'S BEEN
MARKED THEALENDAR EARLY.
COULDN'T WAIT  TO THESE
GAMES.
JON: A SWING■ MISHE■■÷■p■4■1■p#.
VERLANDER GETS■■,p■■ HIS FIRST
STRIKEOUT.
DAVID: WELL, HE HAD HIM SWINGING
OVER THE SLIDER AWAY.
LAID ON THE FASTBALL.
HE'S TIMING UP.
JUSTIN VERLANDER, TWO-SEAMER UP.
>> THE ZONE AT 96.
LOOK AT HOW HIS FINGERS ARE
cL THAT B■/A>A>A>
AWAWG@n■>H>H>H>H>■í■;■;:■■=■■■■.
LUKE VOIT HAS TROUBLE CATCHING
UP WITH THAT ONE.
JON: STILL 36 YEARS OLD AND
JUSTIN VERLANDER WILL COME AT
YOU WITH THE POWER.
DAVID: AND OFF THAT PLANE, THE
BREAKING BALL HE CAN THROW UP
THERE, YOU'VE GOT TO WAIT AND
YOU'VE GOT TO TRUST YOAN TRY TOF
THE FIELD.
HE'S JUST GOT SO MANY WEAPONS.
JON: SANCHEZ SOFTLY HITS ONE OUT
TO SHORT.
CORREA COLLECTS.
AND THAT'S THE THIRD OUT.
VERLANDER PITC AROUND THE
HE■.■■■■■ASTROS WILL COME UPK#K.
ó■ó■■  For the love of,
and trail dust.
and no roads.
For the love of
hunting, fishing,
and working the land.
presernd■1 of conser■■■■
úing TrOff-roles.
foing up American soil.
TRACKER Off Road.
Built for love of co
(PAUL)
How do we tell people they get
the best of both worlds
with Sprint?
(SASSBOT)
How about we get two-sport
legend, Bo Jackson...
(BO)
Sup?
Guys - you don't need me  JuD
a great price with Sprint.
(SASSBOT)
Yes! You can get an Unlimited
plan and a super cool all new
Samsunfor ju■ l ■ l h.
On an LTE advanced newtork
that's up to 2X faster than
before.
(EVELYN)
Bo does...know.
(VO)
Switch and get an
Unlimited plan with the
new Galaxy S10e lease included
for just $35 per month.
No trade-in required.
For people with hearing loss,
visit Sprintrelay.com
>> KEVIN CARSON IN STUDIO.
LET'S -- CONNORS IN STUDIO.
LOOK AT ALBERTO.
5-4-3 DOUBLE PLAY.
NO SCORE IN BALTIMORE.
BY THE WAY, DAVIS BATTING SIXTH
IN THE LINEUP.
0 FOR HIS LAST 44.
JON: OH, BABY.
THE RECORD IS -- IS IT 0 FOR 45
OR 56?
WE'LL DOUBLE -- OR 46?
WE'LL DOUBLE-CHECK.
DAVID: I THOUGHT WE HAD A KHRIS
DAVIS HIGHLIGHT.
JON: KHRIS DAVIS WITH A K, NOT A
C.
OFF TO A SLOW START OFFENSIVELY.
12TH OUT OF 15 TEAMS IN RUNS PER
GAME.
GEORGE S YOU TALK ABOUT
A GUY WHO WILL ATTACK YOU RIGHT
FROM THE JUMP.
HE GOE AGAINST MASAHIRO
TANAKA.
DAVID: TANAKA IS A GUY THAT'S
NOT GONNA GIVE IN.
NOT GONNA GIVE YOU THAT
FOUR-SEAMER ON A FASTBALL COUNT.
HE'S GONNA TRY TO GET YOU TO
EXPAND OUT OF THE ZONE.
JON: IN TODAY'S WORLD OF TEASING
THE STRIKE ZONE, THAT'S THE
THING THAT HE REALLYODO, ESPECI.
IN THE AIR, DOWN THE RIGHT SIDE.
SLICE FOUL.
DAVID: THAT FIRST -- IF THAT■■
ANYTHINGAVING A)IKE TELL Y■■
GEORGE S5■■THEqq■■ R■,FIRSTz  PA
4[■[ YOU AN■  ALERT, AS THE
OPPOSING PITCHER, RIGHT OUT OF
THE CHUTE.■■■■■■H■■H■8@■@
JON: SPRINGER GOES THROUGH THIS
ROUTINE.
WILL GO TO A.J. HINCH, THE
MANAGER, PREGAME AND HAND HIM,
LIKE, A SET OF ABOUT FOUR BATS.
A.J. WILL JUST KIND OFEEL THEM
OLD THEM UP AND DOWN AND
SAY USE THIS IN THE GAME.
USE THIS ASACKUP.
THIS IS FOR B.P.
HITTER, RIGHT?WIN-WIN FOR THE
IF HE DOESN'T GET HIT■■■■■■■■■■■
■■■■■■■■■■ MANAGER THAT DAY.
IT WAS YOUR FAULT.
BAD CHOICES.
JON: BUT THE MANAGER IS ALSO
A PLAYERHEéñ7ñ>ñ>/Tñ>■■G IT W■
■■k8>÷■8■=■7■2■8-÷LIKE THE■pDb■W
WHAT I MEAN?
DAVID: AUY LIKE ME, HE'S GOING
TO SAY, NOT GONNA MATTER TODAY,
BUDDY.
YOU'RE FACING VERLANDER.
JON: HA HA!
TAPPED SOFTLY BUT FOUL.
2-2 ON THE LEADOFF MAN.
NO SCORE.
WE'RE IN THE BOTTOM OF THE
FIRST.
AT MINUTE MAID PARK.
A RARE NIGHT WITH THE ROOF OPEN.
THIS IS A COOL BALLPARK.
ONE OF THE THINGS I LIKE ABOUT
IT IS THAT, WHEN THE ROOF IS
OPEN, IT FEELS LIKE AN OUTDOOR
BALLPARK.
DAVID: YEAH.
THEY'RE NOT ALL LIKE THAT.
YOU'RE IN AN■■■■■A■FEEL LIKE
NOT NAMING NAMES.
THAT ONE MISSES.
SPRINGER, THEN ALTUVE, THEN
BREGMAN, AGAINST TANAKA.HHHHHH
HH AND GOHHHTHE COUNTS A LOT OF'
PAYOFF PITCH.
ON THE GROUND TO SHORT.
TORRES COLLECTS IT.
ONE UP, ONE DOWN.
IT BRINGS UP THE FORMER M.V.P.,
2017.ALTUVE.
HEGF■■■,8
M■C■WB7B7■7j7j7ROE .
THIS■■■■÷■÷■÷■÷ GUY, SIX-TIME A.
WON THREE BATTING TITLES.
HE IS COMING OFF OFF-SEASON KNEE
SURGERY.
IOT TO CALL THEp ASTROS-RED SOX
LCS.
NIGHTS  AFTER SOME OF GAMES.
HE ENDED UP, OVER T
■m■■■■■I@I■■I■]■]■Q■@■Q@Q@]RIGHT
KNEECAP.
THT IT WAS, PARTIALLY
NEECAP.
HE ENDED UP HAVING A SURtgrg■gDE
YET.
HURT■aOTALLY BACK.
DAVID: YEAH.
THOSE KNEE INJURIES ARE FUNNY.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET THE STRENGTH
BACK.
THEN THE MENTAL HURDLE YOU'VE
GOT TO COME OVER.
THE MENTAL ASPECT IS REALLY■■■
RINDS IT.a
ARE IF H HITTING■■
JON: I THINK YOU MA PNDING ALWA■
GOOD
IF YOU NEED A HIT,OU JUST --
HE'D BE THE GUY.E■■■■@■@Ñ@ñ@Ñ@■@
DAVID: YEAH.
AND HE'S SWINGING TOO.
FROM A CATCHER'S STANDPOINT,
IT'S NOT LIKE HE'S WORKING THE
AT-BAT AND HE'S REALLY SMART.
NO.
HE SEES BALL, GETS BALL.
HE'S HACKING, PUTTING A GREAT
SWING ON IT.
ONLY QUALIFIE HITTER TO
T0 300 OR BETTER IN EACH OF THE
LAST FIVE SEASONS.
THREE BATTING TITLES OVER THAT
STRETCH.
PUNCHES THAT TO RIGHT.
RIGHT AT JUDGE.
DAVID: YEAH.
WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT
EXPANDING ON PITCHES.
AND THIS GUY'S GOT THE ULTIMATE
BAT TO LLS.
OFF T DIVING A LITTL■ ■
BIññññññññññ OUTSIDE.ññññññññññ÷
b ■7?á]]■@■■/ THE ONE END
BUT CAN STILL REACH THAT BALL,
DOWN AWAY, UP AND AWAY REALLY.
AND FLY OUT, HIT A DECENT LINE
DRIVE TO RIGHT FIELD.
IF THAT'S IN Aón■L■■áY=■8■8■43/=
■ HAS GOT■2■4■ ■ ■d■11F@11ahA@A@
AND HERE IS ALEX BREG
GOT A CHANCE TO TALK TO HIM
PREG
HE IS ABOUT AS ENGAGING AS IT
GETS.
REALLY GOOD PLAYER.
NOT SHY.
HE'S GOT SOME SWAG, AS THE KIDS
LIKE TO SAY.
DAVID: DEFINITELY GOT SOME SWAG.
JON: ROCKET TO CENTER FIELD!
COMING ON, GARDNER DIVES.
CAN'T MAKE THE PLAY.
AND THAT'S A BASE H■÷m÷■÷■>■÷
I MEAN, HE HIT THAT RIGHT ON THE
BUTTON!
DAVID: AND ITS EASY TO HAVE --
IT'S EASY TO HAVE SWAG WITH A
SWING LIKE THAT.
WATCH THIS LITTLE LOW WITH HIS
HANDS.
BLOOP!
RIGHT THERE.
JUST STAYS RIGHT WITH THE
BASEBALL.
TRYING TO TAKE THAT KNOB
STRAIGHT UP THE MIDDLE.
KEEP THAT BACK HAND AND BACK
ELBOW TIGHT.
NICE TRY BY GARDNER.
I THOUGHT HE HAD A BEAT ON IT,
FROM OUR PERSPECTIVE HERE.
JUST SHORT HOP OF HIS GLOVE.
THAT'S A BETTER THAN CENTER
FIELDER -- VETERAN CENTER
FIELDER THROWING HIS BODY IN
FRONT OF THAT SO IT H■R EX■■■■■■
IT VELOCITY.
AND HERE IS MICHAEL BRANTLEY.■■
DAVID: THAT'S WHAT MAKES TANAKA
SPECIAL RIGHT THERE.
A LITTLE 0-0 BACK-DOOR LITTLE
CUTTER TO A TOUGH HITTER LIKE
BRANTLEY WHERE YOU'RE TRYING TO
GET AHEAD OF HIM.
THIS GUY'S GOT SUCH COMMAND OF
THE DISH.
I'D LOVE THIS SIGN FOR THE
AS IN THE OFF
MICHAEL BRANTLE IS A TRUERO,
HE I■!■■■■A■A■■■■■■■■
ELL, THE THING WITH
BRANTLEY IS THAT H■■■
OFF THEñv■v■áéb■b■b<b DOUD íU■■u
THAT WILL HIT YOUb■CXkXkXkXk■Ûz
PROBABLY 20 HOMERS IN THAT
RANGE.
AND 35-PLUS DOUBLES.
NIGHTMARE,7■ígggó■F■/■/■'S THE Ñ
I WAS TELLING YOU EARLIER, THIS
GUY'S -- HE'S GOT A SMALL HOLD
DOWN IN A WAY.
IT'S LIKE A PERFECT PITCHER'S
PITCH.
HE'S GOT NICE LENGTH.
HE'LL TAKE IT THE OTHER WAY OR
UP THE MIDDLE.
BUT YET HE'S GOT A OWER
IN.
YOU GOTTA GO UP AND IN.
THE ONLY REAL HOLE, UP BY HIS
HAND.
PROBABLYGHEST PITCH FOR
A PITCHER TO MAKE.
JON: TO THE RIGHT SIDE.
AND THAT ONE COLLECTED BY
LEMAHIEU.
AND THATTHAT.
Every curve, evevation, v
A product of mastery.
Lease the 2019 ES 350 for
$389 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
♪
Intr■ ■ çohn'ú>8epperoni.
The pizza pepperoni fans
have been craving,■■■2■22
with 30% more peppthraditi s
and get any large
for just 12 bucks.
BETTER INGREDIENTS.
BETTER PIZZA. PAPA JOHN'S.
[ telephone rings ]
[ Client ] - Hey Maya.
Hey! You still thinking
about opening your own shop?
Every day.
I think there are some ways
to help keep you on track.
And closer to home.
Edward Jones grew to a trillion
dollars in assets under care,
by thinking about your
goals as much as you do.
Each day Justin
chooses to walk.
And afte■■■..■xxx■=xxxó
He does it all with
Dr. Scholl's.
Only Dr. Scholl's has
Massaging Gel Insoles
that provide
all-day comfort.
To keep him feeling
more energized.
Scholl'@■Moveccc■B■ ■ ■
Mom! He's Blinking too loud.
Sorry, is that too loud?
You don't need any more hormones
in your house.
That's why you chose Kraft
Natural Cheese.
Made with fresh milk without the
added hormone rbST.
It's Cheese as it should be.
WORK.
WE GO TO THE SECOND IN A
SCORELESS GAME.
NOW TIME FOR PLANNING AHEAD,
BROUGHT TO YOU BY VOYA
FINANCIAL.
CHECK OUT THIS LIST RIGHT HERE.
MOST RECENT TEAMMATES WITH 250
OR MORE STRIKEOUTS IN THE SAME
SEASON.
GARRETT COLE AND JUSTIN
VERLANDER IN 2018.
LAST TIME TO DO IT, BACK TO
2002, THE BIG UNIT AND SCHILL.
THEN RYAN AND TANANA.
MCDOWELL AND TIANT.
THEN DRAISAITL AND4%■%
THEN TOWED RAMSEY AND<7,■EX■s■■
ON.■ ■vvvv8#s GLERRES NOW.■á
DAVID: I ALWAYS PICKó%ó% BR
MCCANN,Y GOOD BUDDY, WHO
CATCHES THESE GAMES.
I ALWAYS PICK HIS BRAIN.
HE SAYS THEY ARE RELENTLESS IN
THEIR WORK ETHIC AND
PREPARATION.
THE WAY HE READS A SWING,
JUSTIN VERLANDER, TALKING
SITTING ON THE BENCH, HE SAYS
THAT GUY WAS TAKING RIGHT
THERE.
HE READS BODY LANGUAGE.
JON: IN THE AIR SHALLOW RIGHT.
IS CHARN ■■■■■UT.
BACK TO KEVIN CONNORS.
KEN: NATS AND PHILS.
PHILLY THREAT INN IN  FIRST,
TW THREATENING, TWO ON.
THEN J.T. REALMUTO LOOKING.
BRYCE HARPER WALKED EARLIER IN
THE INNING.
THEY ARE SCORELE IN PHILLIES.
A'S-ORIOLES, HOW ABOUT THAT?
TREY MANCINI AGAIN ARCS SOLO
SHOT, HIS FIF■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■A■■
STS GREG BIRD NOW.■
THERE'S A STRIKE TO THE
YANKEES' FIRST BASEMAN.
ONE OUT, BASES CLEAR.
THE ASTROS■■■■■■■■■■■■■N.
THAT SHIFTS■■■8■■■■■■■■■SS■■■■■
NOW.
THERE IS■■ A LOOK AT IT.
NOW YOU SEE BREGMAN ISUT  ■■7■7■
HE PLAYED■#úú8 SHORTÑE■) IN■/■■
SOME AT THE BIG LEAGUE LEVEL.
BIRD WAVES AT THAT ONE.■■777■■■T
ABOUT DISSECTING A HITTER, THIS
ISi>■v■ IMPRESSIVE.■sñ÷■T UP AW
FASTBALL PAINT, MIDDLE-AI.
WHAT AND THEN DROP THAT UNCLE
CHARLIE ON HIM.
THAT IS TOUGH TO HIT RIGHT
THERE.
GREG BIRD, 1-2-3.
JON: VERLANDER WITH FIVE SWINGS
AND MISSES.
HE HAS THROWN 20 PITCHES, 17
STRIKES.
WE L THA■ I THINK.
I'M NOT A MATH GUY, BUT I'M
JUST SAYING.
DAVID: A BIG FAN OF STRIKES.
I AM DEFINITELY■ NOT A■1 MAST G
SLIDM1■HE BEAD■@ OVER AND FIGUR
THATOUT.
DAVID:■ WHAT IS AN■ ABACAS.
JON: LEMAHIEU F■o17■;■I■IKI■[ç[
THIS GUY SIGNE6■■/g■g■W■■2■2■■■■
■&■&■m
, GOOD BAT TO BALL SKILLS AS WE
TALKED ABOUT.■■■t■YS THE NAME■T
GAME TODAY.
DAVID: NO DOUBT.
HIS,÷C ARE PRETTY
PROFESSIONAL■>■=>■
)VE A GUY THAT WILL GRIND
T-BAT, AND HE WILL TAKE TO
YOU RIGHT.
IT IS RARE THAT A GUY'S
STS <g<g■■ SIDE
OF THE÷■
HE CAN HIT IT■■■T SIDE
WITH THE BEST OF THEM.
BUT ALL KNOW ABOUT THE SHORT
PORCH TO RIGHT AT YANKEE
STADIUM.
THAT WIL MORE
UN POWER FOR HIM.
A SOLID, ALL-AROUND PLAYER.
I HAVE ADMIRED HIM FROM THE
OTHER SIDE A LONG TIME.■
JON: TAPPER BACK TO THE MOUND
THAT VERLANDER HANDLES.
THE THROW IS LOW, BUT HE IS
OUT.
THE YANKEES GO 1-2-3.
should be.
What about this?
Changing your plans.
Yeah.
Run with us.
Search "John Deere 1 Series"
for more.
♪♪
Taco Bell invites you to a world
where you'll find
all your Taco Bell favorites
in one amazing $5 box.
The $5 Chalupa Cravings Box
from Taco Bell's new
Cravings Value Menu.
Value ■}q2■■22■■■■■á
[bong]
♪Hi. I'm René.
And for me there's■
winner. Crunch.
= Delicious 100% real chocolate
embracing the lightness
of crispy rice.
Crunch. The chocolate bar
all Americans love.
Introducing The All-New Chevy
Silverado.
It's the official truck of
calloused hands
and elbow grease.
The official truck of getting to
work,■■ ■ ■ ■ getting to work.
Of late nights,
and date nights.
It's the official truck of
homecoming,
and coming home.
The All-New Chevy Silverado.
The strongest, most advanced
Silverado ever.
It's the official truceal
people.■■■■■■■■
JON: WELCOME BACK TO MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL ON ESPN.
TONIGHT'S TELECAST PRESENTED BY
USAA.
WEDNESDAY ON ESPN+, MIKE TROUT
AND THE ANGELS HOSTS CHRISTIAN
YELICH AND THE BREWERS IN THEIR
SERIES FINALE AT 10:00 EASTERN,
DOWNLOADING THE APP ON GOING ON
ESPNPLUS.COM.
THERE WE GO.
THE SHIN-SOO CHOO IS READYÑ1Ñ1
THE■■Rh■2HOO-CHOO IS@■■H■XJ REA
OUT THERE.■R■RLR■R@@@■■■■■■■■■■
DAVID: RYAN DEMPSTER TOLD ME A
STORY ONE TIME.
ICIO P -- LOU
PINIELLA SAID I DON'T KNOW.
HIT THEM UP THERE ON THE
N.
JON: MINUTE MAID, ORANGE JUICE.
ON THE GRO÷m÷m÷m.
ONE UP, ONE DOWN.
LET CHECK IN WITH KEVIN
CONNORS.
KEN: WE ARE ON THE BOARD IN
PHILLY.
NATS PHILS.
THE FORMER CAL STATE FULLERTON.t
TITAN, KURT SUZUKI, HITS THAT
ONE TOWARD THE CHEESE STEAKS.
TWO-RUN SHOT, NUMBER ONE ON THE
JOE YOU GO■■■   ■ ■■■ ■FR■■■[í[@
TANAKA AGAINST GURRIEL.
THAT ONE IN THERE FOR A STRIKE.
WELL, OUR MAN, AARON BOONE, OUR
NAGER ON THEX■ú■■■■■
■ AS GOOD AS IMITATING
BATTING STANCES AS PITCHING
MOTIONS AS ANYONE I HAVE BEEN
AROUND■■■■■■■,■■OT INCLUDI■(■■■■
DAVID: RIGHT.
JON: BUT BOONEY IS PRETTY GOOD.
SO ONE DAY -- AS THAT ONE IS
HIT IN THE AIR FOUL RIGHT SIDE.
TANAKA IS WALKING PAST HIM, AND
HE SAID WHAT DO YOU HAVE ON MY
RANDOM JAPANESE RIGHT-HANDER?
HE WASN'T ACTUALLY DOING
TANAKA.
HE WAS DOING JUST GENERIC
JAPANESE PITCHER.
AND TANAKA WAS LIKE PRETTY
GOOD.o■■!o■YY■9■9■■■■■■■■■■
DAVID: I LIKE THE SQUAT
AFTERWARDS AND THE PAUSE.
SWING AND A MISS, AND GURRIEL ú.
GOES DOWN ON STRIKES.
BACK TO THE STUDIO.
CHRIS DAVIS UPDATE. KARL: IF YO
FAN, HERE IS DAVIS, 0-44 DATING
BACK TO LAST SEASON, NOW ZERO
FOR HIS LAST
EC AT-BA
O SLEDDIN.
DAVID: THAT MY STOMACH
HURT.
JON: REDDICK HOOKS ONE FOUL.
JOSH REDDICK COMES TO THE
PLATE, A BIG RIC FLA
YOU CAN HEAR THEM AL WHHOING
IN THEROUND.
DAVID: "WRESTLEMANIA" WAS
LAST NIGHT, WASN'T IT?
JON: YES.
IN NEW JERSEY.
IS THAT WHERE WE WAS, METLIFE?
DAVID: YEAH.
JON: THEY HAVE THE THREE
FIELDERS ON THE RIGHT SIDE.
TO THE LEFT OFD BASE. RD,
YOU CR THE
WHOO!
SORRY.
I AM NOT SUPPOSED TO BE
PARTICIPATING, AM I.
OUT TOWARD LEFT CENTER.
HERE IS GARDENER COMING ON AND
OWN EASY 1-2-3 INNING FOR
TANAKA.
WE ARE HEADED TORD
HERE.
OF IS OPEN, GORGEOUS
Alr me to go.
what if I...
me home?
[♪♪]
what if I...
What if we lost track of time?
[♪♪]
What if we took a leap of faith?
Whoo-hoo!
What if you...
missed my flight next week?
[♪♪]
The All-New RAV4.
Toyota.
go places.
JON: WELL, TOMORROW ON ESPN,.
RED SOX HOME OPENER AT FENWAY
PARK.
CHRIS SALE GETS THE START FOR
THE DEFENDING CHAMPS AS THEY
N THE BLUE JAYS AT■■
EASTERN.
IT WILL BE A BIG DAY IN BOSTON.
HERE FOR T/ YANKEES AND THE
ASTROS.
BOTH GAMES ARE ON ESPN AND THE
SO■)■m■m IT WILL BE FRlQ■÷■÷%h
AND GARDENER.
JUSTIN VERLANDER SO FAR MOWING
THEM DOWN.■ñ■P
DAVID: I FINALLY GOT TO TELL
CLINT FRAZIER MY STORY.
MY FIRST EVER DRAFT MEETING I
GOT TO GO INTO WAS IN BOSTON.
I WALK IN, AND THEY ARE GOING
OVER SOME PLAYERS THAT ARE
POTENTIAL FIRST ROUNDERS.
THERE IS A LIST UP THERE, AND
THE FIRST PERSON I SEE IS HIM
HITTING TANKERSLEY TO RIGHT
CENTER AND LEFT CENTRAL IN HIGH
SCHOOL.
HE GOT DRAFTED BY THE CLEVELAND
INDIANS IN THAT DRAFT.
IT WAS COOL.
HE SAID I THOUGHT I WAS GOING
TO THE RED SOX.
I JUST HAD A FEELING.
I HAD A FEELING.
IT WAS FUNNY.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT JUST THAT
WHOLE PROCESS.
HIS ROOMMATE WAS TIM HIER'S
SON, WHO IS THE HITTING COACH
FOR THE BOSTON RED SOX NOW.
HE WAS THERE WHEN I WAS THERE.
WENT IS
BACK.■P
JON: HE HAD A COUPLE OF HOMERS
ON SUNDAY IN THEIR 15-3 WIN.
HE HAS SOME SOCK.
DAVID: NO DOUBT.
I KEPTONDERING, THIS IS LIKE
A FIRST ROUNDER NOW?
A LOTMA
CK THEN
w1 SIZE
AND WHATEVER.
N: IT HAS BEEN REPORTED THERE
IS SOME SCOUTING BIAS AGAINST
RED HEADS.
DAVID LLOYD
DAVID: WHERE DID WE HEAR THAT
FROM?
JON: IT IS TRUE.
I AM TELLING YOU, BASEBALL
AMERICA DID A PIECE ON.
NE.
D: WELL, BASEBALL AMERICA
IS PRETTY SPOT-ON.
HOW MANY ARE THERE, BOOG?
RATIO IS NOT HEAVY.
JON: WE ARE LIKE UNICORNS.
DAVID: THAT IS RIGHT.
YOLOW IS WAY B■■■ T
HAVING A TOUGH HAIR
NI
■ TR]
■÷ YOU ARE ALWAYTO
RUN INTO THAT.
DAVID: I AM.
JON: 3-2 ON THE WAY.
DAVID: THEY LIKE THAT UP SIDE.
HE HAS GREAT UP SIDE.
I THINK HE HAS PUT IT TOGETHER.
HE HAS CONTINUED TO DEVELOP.
BUT THAT IS A NICE S?u
STROKE.
HE KEEPS THE HAND■p
BODY.
A LOT LIKE ALEX BREGMAN,
KEEPING THEM NICE AND TIED.
THAT LOWER BODY■■■ WORKS WELL I
SYNC WE HANDS.
THAT GUY'S A
JON: A BASEBALL RAT.
SWING AND A MISS.
THAT IS NASTY.
JUSTIN VERLANDER, LOCK INSIDE
SO FAR.
DAVID: THERE AIN'T MUCH YOU CAN
DO WHEN YOU ARE DROPPING THE
3-2 BREAKING BALL.
THIS GUY HAS■■■ IN HIS BACK
#■■■A■■■■■■UP
AND UP TO DOWN ALL NIGHT.
YOU SEE HERE THE FASTBALL UP
AND AWAY, TO THE BREAKING BALL
DOWN.
ABSOLUTELY DROPPING OFF THE
TABLE.
AND D.J. LEMAHIEU GOING UP FOR
THE SLIDER, AND DOWN AND AWAY.
YOU GET FRAZIER, THE FASTBALL
IS UP.
AND THEN HE DROPS A 3-2 NASTY
BREAKING BALL RIGHT THERE.
VE TO TIP YOUR CAP TO THE
HALL OF FAMER.
JON: OR MAN, ROB FRIEDMAN, THE
PITCHING NINJA ON TWITTER, HE
WILL BE DOING STUFF FOR US ALL
SEASON LONG, SHOWING THEIR
FOUR-SEAM FASTBALL AND THE
CURVEBALL AND HOW IT COMES OUT
OF THE THE SAME SPOT.
■n■nvíq■'#HH!  ■■8■p■2 WHA■8#a#
DAVID: THAT IS WHAT HE HAS
GOING FOR HIM, AND HE KNOWS IT.
HE IS STILL ONE OF THE BEST IN
THE GAME AT READING SWINGS.
MAER IS PHEN TOO.
I ASKED HIM ONE TIME, BUT HE
WOULDN'T LET ME IN ON THE
SECRET.
HE CAN SEE THEIR APPROAC■>■>■>■A
Xzpp■pf■f■ SEEING WHAT THE FOUL
IS TELLING THEM OR BODY
LANGUAGE OF AR.
THAT IS WHAT A CATCHER USUALLY
INFERS.
IF YOU HAVE A PITCHER DOING
THAT, IT IS GOIN FUN ■1■8yyñsñpa
JON: LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT
STATCAST A.I., POWERED BY
A.W.S.
MOST SWINGS AND MISSES, JUSTIN
VERLANDER BY FAR, VERSUS,■■ COL
AND DEGROM.■÷■1■1
DAVID: SOMETHING I HAVE
BELIEVED. ■■■ EVEN
THOUGH IT IS NOT AS PREVALENT
IN OUR GAME AS ■■ MUCH, IT IS
STILL IMPORTANT TO ME.
JON: I THINK WHAT THE YANKEES
HAVE DONE KIND OF SUMS UP WHERE
THE SPORT IS, AND THAT IS THE
NEW YORK YANKEES LAST YEAR HAD
THE HARDEST AVERAGE FASTBALL
■■AN■ DIDN'T TH■ THAT
■■■ THAT IS WHAT
U ARE SEEING.
IF YOU GET ONE, IT ISCOMI■
YOU ■■■■■■■■■■■■■■4■■■4■■■■■■ M
AND YOU ARE JUST NOT GETTING
THEM AS FREAK ■■■ AUSED■■■■■■
TO T■■ W■ S
T
T THEY ARE■■■■■DRANTS.
THEY KNOW WHAT THE■
SECONDARY STUFF.
THE YANKEES■■■■■■■■■■■■oo■■■■■ó
SECONDARY PITCH THEY THROW MORE
AND MORE BECAUSE THEY HAVE THAT
JON: I TELL YOU, IT IS  OCKET T
INTERESTING TO ME WITH A GUY
LIKE GARDENER UP HERE, THAT
THEY PLAY THE SHIFT.
OK, THEY ARE PLAYING TO THE DAT
HAS SOME SOCK TO HIM, BUT DON'T@
BUT THEY ARELAYING THREE
FIELDERS ON THE RIGHT■j S
THEY OBVIOUSLY HAVE INFORMATION
TO BACK IT UP, AND HE IS GOING
INTO
DAVID: YOU AREN RIGHT
GU■■■■■■■■■■ ■ ■■■■■■L
WEAPONS WITH THE BAT.
LET'S PITCH HIM TO WHERE WE
WANT HIM TO HIT IT.
WE ARE GOING TO PLAY HIM THERE.
THEY ARE SITTING DOWN IN THEIR
MEETINGS BEFORE GAMES, AND THAT
IS WHAT THEY ABOUT.
JON: GOT IT.
TO -- SO IT IS NOT PASSIVE.
THEY ARE DICTATING THAT.
DAVID: I THINK FOR THEIR
HERS TO EXECUTE CERTAIN
PITCHES, THATS EXACTLY WHAT
JON: AND NOT EVERY TEAM IS  ■y■@
DOING IT.
>> AT TAMPA BAY I NEVER GOT
PITCHED IN.
THEY ONLY PITCHED ME IN AND
PLAYED ALL THEIR LEFT FIELDERS
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
I WAS LIKE WAIT, THIS IS
OP■ I AM USED■
KIND OF THREW ME FOR A LOOP.
AND I COULDN'T HIT TO BEGIN
WITH, SO IT REALLY DIDN'T
MATTER.
ALEX COBB THROWING ME SINKERS
IN, AND CHANGE-UPS IN.
IT WAS FRUSTRATING.
YOUARD GROUND BALL, THERE ARE T
THERE.
JON: GET IT IN THE AIR.
DAVID: I DIDN'T KNOW THE
LAUNCH ANGLE THING.
I WAS JUST FOCUSING ON THE
CONTACT THING.
NICE BLOCK.
JON: NICE BLOCK.
DAVID: ATTA BOY.
YOU ARE ON TOP OF IT.
ROBINSON CHIRONOS IS TEXTBOOK
HERE.
BREAKING BAL SHORT.
READY TO FRAME IT.
FRON HIM AND POPS UP ON HIS ■@
FEET.
REALLY LIKE HIS CATCHING GAME.
JON: CENTERED IT.
I AM SPENDING WAY TOO MUCH TIME
AROUND YOU.
DAVID: NICE BLOCK, YEAH.
LEAVE TH1 STUFF TO ME,■)YOU WILL
RIGHT.
JON: 3-2 NOW.■■■  ■ ■2@
THE ASTROS LAST YEAR, THEY ARE
T THAN THE TEAM THAT
WON IT ALL.
LAST YEAR RUN PREVENTION
WALLACE THE ANCHOR FOR A.J.
HINCH'S GROUP.
THEY ALLOWED THE FEWEST RUNS IN
THE MAJORS LAST YEAR, AND TO DO
IT PLAYING IN THE AMERICAN
LEAGUE IS IMPRESSIVE.
WHEN YOU ARE THE TEAM THAT■■■
ALLOWS THE FEWEST RUNS PER GAME
IN THE A.L. SINCE 1981.
BOUNCER TO RIGHT.
AND IT GETS THROUGH.
WITH URSHELA ON THE MOVE, HE
IT FOUND A SPACE.
ON THE EIGHTH PITCH OF THE
AT-BAT, A GARDENER SINGL IS A R
AT-BAT BY GARDENER HERE.
THIS IS THE GREAT THING ABOUT A
3-2 COUNT AND MOVING THE BASE
RUNNERS.
YOU GET A NICE FOUR-SEAMER
AWAY.
YOU KNOW YOU ARE
THAT.
WATCH THEM START TO COVER.
IT IS RIGHT WHERE CORREA IS
STANDING, BUT HE HAS TO COVER
THE BAG■÷
Ö■8■8■8■
SER STEALING.
NO■■■■■ FIRST AND.
GARDENERNG HEY, YOU
HAVE TO PLAY ME STRAIGHT UP.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
JON: REGGI■1QÑ■vBvBvBvBv■■vbv■■T
PLAY ME STRAIGHTM■>wg[■';@;@;x12
■■■+1■■■
■
AND NOW HERE'S JUDGE.
THE YANKEES WITH A THREAT.
CHECK SWING, DIDN'T■;■; GO.
THAT IS1T2T VANOVER DOWN
THERE.
DAVID: THAT IS A NICE TAKE
RIGHT THERE.
YOU GET THE FASTBALL FOR A
BALL.
THEN THE SLIDER, JUST DOWN.
THAT WAS A REALLYTAKE BY
AARON JUDGE.
JON: THAT GOT A PIECE OF
DAVID: THAT WAS A SPINNER THAT
THERE.■S■RHROW A■■lú]ahh■■ú■>/d■
JUDGE KNOWS.
HE IS LIKE I GOT AWAY WITH ONE
THERE.
JON: JUDGE IN HIS FIRST■v AT-BA
CAREER HIT AGAINST VERLANDER.
BEFORE TONIGHT HE HAD BEEN
0-13.
DAVID: THIS IS THE MOMENT WHERE
IF ARE A HITTER AND THE
OPPOSING TEAM, YOU NEED TO PAY
ATTENTION.
THIS IS WHERE THE RUBBER HITS
THE ROAD.
THIS IS WHERE JUSTIN VERLANDER
IS GOING TO GO, OK I AM GOING
TO FIGURE OUT THE NUMBERS.
WHAT DO THE NUMBERS SAY HOW TO
GET THIS GUY OUT?
I AM GOING TO THE SLIDER.
THEY ARE GOING TO MAKE AARON
JUDGE IN KEY SITUATIONS HIT THE
SLIDER.
GOING TO DO?OW WHAT HE IS  ■■z
IS HE GOING SHORT SLIDER OR
FASTBALL OUT OF THE ZONE?
JON: RUNNER ON THE GO, AND
GARDENER IS SAFE.
HE GOT A GREAT JUMP THAT TIME.■ú
DAVID: GREAT TIME TO RUN THERE,
TOO.
A BIG PAY-OFF PITCH IN A BIG
SITUATION THERE TRYING TO STAY
OUT OF THE DOUBLE PLAY IF HE
DOES HIT IT ON THE GROUND.
HUGE JUMP BY GARDENER.
NICE THROW BY CHIRINOS.
HE HAD NO CHANCE.
JON: WHAT COMES HERE?
DO YOU GO CHASE WITH A SLIDER
OR STAY WITH SOMETHING IN THE
ZONE?
DAVID: THIS IS THE TOUGHEST
SITUATION IN BASEBALL FOR ME,
ESPECIALLY AS A HITTER.
I HAVE SO MANY■/ OPTIONS AS■2■8
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO HAVE BEAT
YOU, LUKE VOIT OR AARON JUDGE?
I AM GOING W LUKE VOIT ALL
DAY EVERY DAY.
FOR ME, HE IS GOING TO HIT MY
PITCH.
WHATEV■÷■÷■÷■÷■÷■÷■÷■÷■÷■8■8■8■.
■LIDER DOWN+ AWAY.■;■;■;D:■■■■■E
SEEING HERE.
I MIGHT GO HEATER UP.L■
S WHTHE EXPERT
■■ I AM THE IDIOT.■b■■@■ú■@■5NA
THAT IS ME.
I AM THE PLAY BY PLAY GUY AS
WELL.
BACK TO YOU IN THE STUDIO.
KEN: YANKEES THREATENING,
DODGERS THREATENING HERE IN
FIRST INNING.
CODY BELLINGER, .455 ON THE
YEAR.
LOOK AT THE HUSTLE DOWN THE
MI■LAS.TTER IS A.J. POLLOCK@1@1
AN R.B.I. DOUBLE.
WHERE WE ARE.  2AT T■■
DAVE ROBERTSON, CLAYTON KERSHAW
ISO MAKE ANOTHER REHAB
START AT DOUBLE-A TULSA
TOMORROW.
■■■
DODGERS GETTING
HEALTHIER.
MAN,RING.
■2 LINEUP RIGHT NOW IS PRETTY
CIOUS.x8■8■8■8■1÷8:/■1N1■v/ve>>
DDLE■> OF é8■íS■■■■■Y,U■
AND I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT THEPRODU
WAS HAVING AN OFF NIGHT OR WERE
THE DODGERS THAT GOOD.
THEY LOOK AMAZING.
JON: NO DOUBT.
MAN, THAT IS TOUGH RIGHT THERE,
THAT VIEW.
THE SUN POKING THROUGH LIKE
THAT.
THAT IS RIGHT IN HIS EYES,
ISN'T IT?
WOW.■■■>■=■=AA/
HE IS STEPPING OUT BECAUSE HE
CAN'T SEE.
LOOK AT THAT.
DAVID: THAT LOOKS TOUGH.
MAYBE THAT WAS A
MISCOMMUNICATION ON VERLANDER
AND CHIRINOS' PART.
JON: OR MY GOODNESS.
HE GOT ON TOP OF IT ANDÑ> LACED
ONE TO RIGHT, AND THE YANKEES
HAVE THE LEAD AS VOIT WAS ABLE
TO FIGHT THAT THING ■>.
AN R.B.I. SINGLE TO MAKE IT■
1-0.
DAVID: HE PULLED OFF THE SLIDER
EARLY ON FOR THE FOUL BALL.
THEN THE FASTBALL UP■yWAY
HERE
TIGHT■ THERE. ■■■■■■■■■qqd d ■ O
JUST HEAD BEHIND THE BALL.
THAT IS NICE.
PALM UP, PALM DOWN.
BEAUTIFUL SWING BY LUKE VOIT
THERE FOR AN R.B.I., GETTING
JON: VERLANDERX■OpO■■■OQO■;i7■x■
TH WILL BE HIS PITCH
INNING.
THIS IS WHAT THE YANKEES CAN DO
TO YOU.
SANCHEZ POPS IT UP INTO CENTER.
■■■■■■, AND AL IS  ALL THE■÷
THERE.""EEEE■T■
DAVID: DEEP FLIGHT TO RIGHT.
CATCH.COND BASEM■■■V■
DAVID: THAT W2 PIECE ■y, HITTI■4
THOSE ARE THE OPPORTUNITIES
HE'S GOING TO GET.
THE CATCHER THINKING ALONG THE
LINES OF US.
MAKE LUKE VOIT BEAT YOU WITH
AARON■■;P AND SURE ENOUGH,
HE??
THAT WAS A NICE ?á?HITTING, TAKE
HIM.
JON: I THINK RICK SUTCLIFFE IS
WATCHING.
HE'S LEAVING ME A VOICEMAIL.
WHEN WE COME BACK, WE'LL GO 90
FEET WITH ALEX BREGMAN.
That's why we're here
with free hot breakfast.
Bookton.com for
our Price Match Guarantee.
Hampton by Hilton.
Ok everyone!
Our missio
provide complete,
balanced nutrition
for strength and e
Whoo-hoo!
Great-tasting Ensure.
With nine grams of protein
and twenty-six vitamins
and minerals.
Ensure, for strength
and energy.
New lower price.
Wow. That's a lot
of asparagus.
Yeah, you said get
a bunch of asparagus.
Oh, you...
bunch.
I... thought you kinda...
JON: THIS IS 90 FEET WITH THE
ALL-STAR GAME M.V.P., ALEX
BREGMAN.
YOU PLAYED CHESS GROWING UP.
YOU WON THE STATE CHAMPIONSHIP
WHEN YOU WERE 13 OR 14, RIGHT?
ALEX: I PLAYED CHESS.
PLAYED FOR MY HIGH SCHOOL AND
TRAVELED TO NEW YORK CITY.
JON: AND YOU PLAYED IN THE PARK
AND YOU PLAYED A GUY AND?
ALEX: HE WHOOPED MY ASS.
JON: YOU WORE 30 AS A FRESHMAN
IN COLLEGE.
YOU WEAR 2 NOW.
TELL ME WHY?
ALEX: 30 WAS LIKE THE 30 TEAMS
THAT DIDN'T TAKE ME FROM HIGH
SCHOOL.
AND NUMBER TWO, NOW, BECAUSE
JETER AND BECAUSE I'M PLAYING
SECOND.
JON: I GOT A REPORT THAT DAD
GAVE YOU A LITTLE CALL AND SAID
YOU'RE GOING TO PLAY WITH THAT
CHIP ON YOUR SHOULDER AGAIN,
HUH?
ALEX: YEAH, MY DAD TOLD ME I WAS
BEING TOO NICE AT THE BEGINNING
OF THE YEAR.
TOLD ME TO START BEING THE GUY
THAT THE OTHER TEAMS DON'T LIKE.
JON: ARE WE BRINGING JORTS BACK?
ALEX: WE GOT TO BRING THE JORTS
BACK.
THEY BROUGHT US A SWEEP LAST
WEEK AGAINST THE DIVISION
OPPONENT SO WE HAVE TO BRING
THEM BACK EVENTUALLY.
JON: YOU WERE IN THE CAGE.
GEORGE SPRINGER IS PLAYING ONE
OF THEAWESOME SONGS OF
LAST 30 YEARS, BLACK STREET
DR. DRE AND YOU SAID WHAT'S THE
NAME OF THAT SONG?
ALEX: YEAH, I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
IT WAS.
JON: YOU GOT TO COME UP TO OLD
DIGGITY.
30 HOMERS, 50 DOUBLES, 90 WALKS,
10 STEALS.
ONLY ONE OTHER GUY IN THE
HISTORY OF THE GAME HAS DONE
THAT IN A SEASON.
DO YOU KNOW WHO IT IS?
ALEX: LOU GG.
JON: PRETTY GOOD.
ALEX BREGMAN, 90 FEET.
ú■ú BENG OFF.S.■■■
GREAT.■■■■
JOGOT A LOT OF
PERSONALITY.
A LOT OF, YEAH, JUST A LOT OF
CONFIDENCE.
DAVID: I LOVE THE JORTS.
FOR ME, THAT'S NOW A TEAM ROAD
TRIP FOR SURE, RIGHT.
THERE THEY ARE.
[LAUGHTER]
DAVID: I MIGHT HAVE TO GO GET ME
A PAIR FOR OUR BROADCAST
TOMORROW NIGHT.■
JON: HE'S TURNED INTO ONE OF THE
BEST PLAYERS IN THE GAME.
HE'S A BASEBALL RAT.
HE'S ONE OF THOSE GUYS THAT IN
HIGH SCHOOL WAS WAKING UP AT
FINISHING HIS CING, WORKING■
2:00 AND PLAYING BASEBALL UNTIL
10:00 AT NIGHT AND HIS PARENTS
KEPT ASKING HIM, ARE YOU BURNED
OUT, DO YOU WANT TO STOP?
NOPE, THIS IS WHAT I LOVE.
DAVID: THAT'S WHAT IT BOILS DOWN
TO, THE LOVE THAT HE HAS.
IT COMES THROUGH IN THE
REPARATION AND WHAT HE DOES.
IF YOU DON'T LOVE IT LIKE HE
DOES, YOU DON'T SPEND THE TIME
IN THE BATTING CAGES AND AROUND
THE GUYS TALKING BASEBALL.
HE REMINDS ME A LOT OF DUSTIN
PEDROIA WHEN I'M AROUND THEM.
THOSE GUYS IN THE BACK OF THE
PLANE TALKING EVERY ASPECT OF
THE GAME, WHETHER WE JUST WON OR
LOST, AND DISSECTING IT.
THOSE TYPE OF PEOPL■■■ MAKE
EVER■■■■■■■■■■■■■■pppp■■q■■qq■■■
JON: WHEN HE HIT HIS 30TH HOME■a
RUN, A REPORTER ASKED HIM, DID
YOU EVER THINK YOU WOULD HIT 30
HOMERS IN THE BIG LEAGUES?
HE SAID, YEAH.
DAVID: THEHHH■■F(@■■■■■■x BEEN■.
TH b @ @ @ @ b■y■y■yw7wuwu■u■uH.
YO÷■■■■÷÷p DIDN'T?
JON: HE MADE AN ADJUSTMENT LAST
YEAR, PARTIALLY REVEALED DURING
A CONVERSATION WITH ALEX
RODRIGUEZ.
FOa■STBALL, TO THIq■ a■■11■1q 1S
ABOVE, BEATING THE BALL TO THE
SPOT SO THAT SOME OF THOSE
360-FOOT FLY BALLS ALL OF A
SUDDEN WHEN HE'S BEATING THE
BALL TO THE SPOT AND THINKING A
LL ABOVE ON A FOUR-SEAM
BALL, ALL OF A SUDDEN
THEY'RE GOING OUT OFHOOL WAY OFI
NEW-SCHOOL WAY.
BACK IN THE DAY, IT WAS GET ON
TOP OF THE BALL.
YOU SAY THAT TO HITTERS NOW,
THEY'RE LIKE, WHAT?
HIT DOWN THE BALL?
NO.
BUT HE SAYS GET ABOVE IT AND IT
WORKS OUT.
JON: SEVEN STRAIGHT RETIRED BY
MASAHIRO TANAKA.
g your yard.
We do it right, too.
With the right
plants for your region.
So, you stay a step ahead
of spring all season long.
GATORADE ZERO.
ALL THE ELECTROLYTES.
ZERO SUGAR.
♪♪
GET MORE OUT OF ZERO.
(PAUL)
How do we tell people they get
the best of both worlds
with Sprint?
(SASSBOT)
Let's tell everyone that Sprint
offers an Unlimited plan
(VO)nd the new Samsung Gala0e fj
Switch and get an Unlimited plan
with the new Galaxy S10e
lease included.
No trade-in required.
For people with hearing loss,
visit Sprintrelay.com
[outdoor ambiance]
♪
Hi, Mrs. Gorman.
Hey, Theo.
police radio: I have
the stolen vehicle in sight.
[police siren]
♪
■<7■7          ♪
[police siren]
police radio: OnStar,
it's safe to slow it down.
♪
■x       OnStar Advisor:
Mr. Grantham, this is OnStar.
OnStar Advisor:
The police have your vehicle.
Mr. Grantham:
Thank you so much.
A OOK IN ON■p ORIOLES-A'S.UDIO.
CHRIS DAVIS BATTING, ONE SHY OF
0-45, ONE SHY OF TYING THE MAJOR
LEAGUE RECORD.
>> HE GOT UNDER IT.
LONG■ RUN IN FOR PISCOTTY.
PROFAR DROPS THE BALL IN FOUL
TERRITORY SO DAVIS HAS LIFE.
>> GOT A LITTLE SPRINKLE.
A LONG WAY.
>> CERTAINLY A CATCHABLE BALL.
THERE'S GOING TO BE AN ERROR.
>> THEY ONLY MADE ONE ERROR IN
THEIR LAST EIGHT GAMES.
CHAPMAN SHOULD HAVE CAUGHT THE
OTHER BALL.
NOT AN EASY PLAY.
BUT THIS IS THE BIG LEAGUES.
CHAPMAN COULD HAVE -- NOT
CHAPMAN.
>> IT'S IN FOUL TERRITORY.
>> THAT YOUNGSTER WASN'T SURE
WHETHER TO CHEER OR NOT.
>> THEY DO GIVE HIM AN ERROR SO
THAT ALLOWS THE AT-BAT TO
CONTINUE.
HE HAS TWO ERRORS TONIGHT.
LINE DRIVE LEFT FIELD, FALLING,
FALLING AND IN THE GLOVE OF
GROSSMAN.
IT HUNG RE
ENOU HIM.■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
KEVIN:IS■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
VALEZ■■■■U■■■D■ú■ú■ú■■■■■ú■■ú■■,
2 1/2 YEARS -- THE STRIKEOUTS
WERE ALWAYS PART OF IT.
BUT IT USUALLY CAME WITH A LOT
SERVICEABLE.■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■L
■ I CAN'T IMAGI WHAT■ 0-40■■■■■■
FEELS LIKE.
YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE GRINDING AT
0-10, LIKE YOU HAVEN'T GOT A HIT
IN A MONTH.
THAT'S A BAD FEELING.
YOU CAN TAKE THE LOW BATTING
AVERAGE AND STRIKEOUTS WITH
HOMERS MIXED IN BUT SOMETHING
WILL RELEASE, ONCE THAT FIRST
ONE FALLS, MAYBE HE'LL GET SOME
CONFIDENCE.
HE'S GOT TO BE GRINDING RIGHT■■■
JON: BIRD PUSHES IT FOUL.
BIRD, WHO STRUCK OUT SWINGING O.
GREG HEALTHY THIS YEAR.
HE'S PLAYED A TOTAL OF 132 GAMES
PROBLEMS WITH■HE■■■■■E@ TO
AND FOOT■■■■ñ/x/■9bz■■■o/0■
■■
FRWITH THE HEATER.
FOLKS, WEDNESDAY, IT'S THE
MASTERS PAR 3 CONTEST FROM
AUGUSTA 3:00 EASTERN, NOON
PACIFIC ON ESPN, ALSO THE ESPN
APP SO YOU CAN WATCH FROM
ANYWHERE.
WE WILL HAVE A FULL BAND THERE
PLAYING THAT PIANO THE■■■■666■6■
YOU PLAYED AUGUSTA, HAVEN'T YOU?
DAVID: I DIDN'T WANT TO BRING IT
UP BUT BEING THAT YOU■ DID, I■
■■■■■■■■AY THAT.
NOT■■■■■POSTALK ABO■■■
I WAS■■ ONE UNDER AFTER O
THROW THAT OUT THERE.?■
SEE IF IT STICKS ANYWHERE.■■■■■■
JON: VERLANDER HOPING FOR A
QUICK INNING HERE.
DELIVERS TO LEMAHIEU.
PRETTY WELL STRUCK CENTER FIELD.
SPRINGER -- TWO DOWN.
BACK TO THE STUDIO WITH KEVIN.
KEVIN: WE SHOWED YOU THE DODGERS
GETTING ON THERçy■yçyQ=■zñyw■■■T
ST. LOUIS HAS JUST TIED THIS
BABY UP.
MARCELL OZUNA,■■■■ IT IN
AROUND■@■@ THE FOUL POLE.
TWO-RUN HOME RUN, HIS SECOND OF
THE YEAR.
JON: THAT WAS @■ R ■■VID:■■■■■■■
■■■■■■■&&■■F■■■ WASLE.■■■■JJJJ @
JON: I KEPT WAIT IT TO
ND IT NEVER■ON# DID.■%;ds■4■?I?G
KS TODAY, REMINDED ME OF
THAT LONGORIA HOME RUN THAT
SNUCK IN RIGHT OVER THE LEFT
FIELD WALLd%%■■%%■&■■&&&&&&K&&&M
TO GO ■8AY■■%■■■■ ■ ■■■■■■■■1 ■
%%  AN■OUR, EXIT
FOR THEOMER.
HUNDREDS OF MILES AWAY.ZING FROM
IT'S A GIFT.
DAVID: BETTER THAN THE ANALYSIS
I'M DOINGK■C■■■#■■■ HE(
N: DID IR  YOU IALLPITCHES SER
DAVID:SEEN YOU DO THAT■■■■■■■■■E
PITCHING UP IN THE ZONE ■& MORE,
THERE'S LESS SLUG UP.
CATCHERS ARE STARTING TO
PRACTICE DECEIVING THAT BALL.
JON: NICE WO T IN.w=Y■÷■y■7AyAyv
GOT JUST ENOUGH■p OF IT.
DAVID: THIS IS WHEN IT PAYS TO
HAVE ALLIGATOR ARMS.
T-REX ARMS.
THIS S RU ON HIM.■á■á
WATCH HIM PULL IT IN HARD OFF
THE LABEL THERE.
WATCH HIS BACK SIDE.■L■L■L=L1■ T
AWAY AND PULLS THOSE HANDS IN
HARD, THROW SOMETHING OUT THERE
TO CENTER FIELD.
JON: HE'S A LITTLE SWAGGY, TOO,
BY THE WAY.
LOOK AT THE SPIKES.
AIR JORDAN HIGH TOP SPIKES.
OH, MY GOSH.
DO THEY MAKE THOSE FOR HIM?
HOW DO YOU FIGURE THEY DO THAT?
DAVID: I DON'T KNOW WHO DID THAT
FOR HIM.
THAT'S WHERE THE GAME HAS
CHANGED.
I BET HE HAS THOSE MADE.
DAVID: THEY tCt;SOME.ñ>ñ>ñ>■2■22
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT.
BUT BACK WHEN I PLAYED -- BACK
WHEN I PLAYED.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE 10 YEARS IN TO
HAVE COOL STUFF LIKE THAT.
YOU HAD TO BE A REAL VETERAN
PLAYER TO HAVE SWAG ON YOUR
SHOES.
I THOUGHT IT WAS THE COOLEST
THING TO HAVE MY NAME ON THE
BACK OF MY SHOES ONE TIME.■■■k■í
JON: VERLANDER KEEPS CHASING THE
AIR JORDANS BACKO FIRST.qú■■■an■
HEATER■■■■■■■■■!■q■AA■■!! TO GI.
YANKEES LEAD IT 1-0 ON A LUKE
VOIT R.B.I.■■úP!@■
TANAKA■  ■s■■■■■■H■!■NDER, TOP E
FOURTH ON A■1WGEOUS■÷fí■÷8■■■■A■
DAVID: YOU REALLY SEE JUSTIN
VERLANDER■■OWN WITH
THE■■■■■hhh ■■H■1■■■■■■TTY QUIC■
■■EEEEE KNOCK.
SLOWING DOWN, EXECUTING THE
PITCH.
GOING BACK TO THE TOP OF THE
ORDE
VERY IMPORTANT OUT HERE FOR■ HI■
JON: VERLANDER, PITCH COUNT UP
TO 73. ■■■pp■■pppppp■■A■■■■■■JJI
GOOD STAB BY BREGMAN.
AND THERE IS, ONE OF THE BEST
ALL-AROUND PLAYERS IN THE GAME
PLAYING OUT.
STICKS THE LANDING, SAVES A HIT.
Get great deals on great gear
at Bass Pro Shops and Cabela's.
Bring the kids
for our free Easter Event
with giveaways, crafts,
an egg hunt,
and a free picture
with the Easter Bunny.
Go online to learn more.
Your Adventure Starts Here
Do you need the most
trusted battery
in your noise cancelling
headphones?
Maybe not.
Maybe you could trust you won't
be next to a loud eater.
(eating potato chips loudly)
Or you could just trust
Duracell. (silence)
♪♪
Let's talk about thisd
when we meet next week.
Edward Jones came to manage
a trillion dollars in assets
under care by nd on whateve.
■■
USAA IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY■7■
■7■ HELP FOR ■■6
AND■■■■AT■■■■■ LEGALZO■1   ■.COW
JOSE7ww■ww7■UVE AT THE PLATE.
IT WILL BE7■■ A7777777 AND
THEN BRANTLE■QQ
ROSSI?
DAVID: SORRY, WHAT DID I DO?
JON: I'M HAVING A LITTLE TROUBLE
SEEING DOWN BECAUSE THE SUN IS
IN MY EYES.
DAVID: I'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE.
I'M■■ FINE.■■V■■VVvv■■■■■■■11■■Y
REALLY SHINING OFF YOUR RED
HAIR, THOUGH.g■C■ggg#■■■■■#■■■■C
JON: I THINK TANAKA'S GOING BACK
TO WORK.
THAT IS HAMMERED AND THAT IS
GONE.
OUTTA HERE!■
IT HIT THE TOP OF THE TRACKS AND
TH YEAH, LEFT THE PARK.
DAVID: YOU DIDN'T NE TO SEE
THAT ONE.
WE HEARD IT.
THAT WAS LOUD.
JOSE ALTUVE TAKES THIS HANGING
SPLIT-FINGER RIGHT DOWN THE
MIDDLE AND DOES EXACTLY WHAT
SUPPOSEç■ ■ ■ ■ ■,t t t t ■■■■@
THERE.
LOOK AT THE ROTATION, THE FRONT
HEEL OPENING ALL THE WAY UP WITH
FOOT.
THOSE HIPS WORKING.
THAT BALL GOT OUTTA HERE IN A
HURRY ON TOP OF THE TRACKS,
BOUNCES OUT.
THAT WAS A ROCKET.ERE.
JON: ALTUVE WITH HIS SECOND.
CAREER HOMER NUMBER 99.
109.1 MI HOUR.
HOW ABOUT THIS ON THE DISTANCE.
448.■ ■■
DAVID: HANGING SPLIT.
YOU DON'T SEE TOO MANY OF THOSE.
THAT'S A HARD PITCH TO HIT WHEN
IT'S GOT THE RIGHT ACTION.
LOOKS LIKE IT WAS LATE ON THE
TEE FOR HIM.■■'■
N:77■777777■7■7■■■■■■■w■w■■■■■■.
AND HE'S FALLEN BEHIND 3-0.
ALEX BREGMAN HAS SINGLED HARD TO
CENTER HIS FIRST TIME UP.
SEVENTH IN THE MAJORS IN O.P.S.
A S■■rrBBB■■wED■■■■7■■T777■ MONd
MAN ABOARD,Y OUT.
KEVIN: K SUZUKI BROKE THE ICE
WITH A TWO-RUN HOMER BUT ODUBEL
HERRARA TIES IT
2-■>■ TOP THE FIFTH
INNING.
MEANTIME, RAYS-WHITE SOX.
BLAKE SNELL WAS OUTSTANDING.
REIGNING A.L. CY YOUNG WINNER,
SIX INNINGS, ONE EARNED RUN, 11
STRIKEOUTS.
10TH CAREER GAME AT LEAST 10 OR
MORE STRIKEOUTS, JUST THIFTH HI.
5-1, TAMPA BAY WINS.
JON: LET'S NOT■■óóY]■■ççç■■■■■■■
"DANCING WITH THE AVID
ROSS,
■NELL■■■■■ IS THE
GUYS I LIKKK■ RIGHT
NOW.
HIS STUFF IS NASTY.
■YK■■K G
JON: H■■■■■■■■■■■■■ BRANTLEY,D
OUT HIS FIRST TIME.
MA+++■■■IRST, NOBODY■■ OUT.
AGIS WILL HAPPEN
TANAKA WHERE HE'LL TRY AND TEASE
THE EDGES OF THE STRIKE ZONE AND
IF HE■■■■+■ç■ç■■■ç+■■■■ETS ■■■+,
K++■■■■++++++TS F
HITTER'S■KKKKKKKVE.
ESPECIALLY WHEN■ THINGS■ TO
GO BAD, YOU GET■■■■■GGG■
■■■■EG■■■■■
TIMID WHEN YOU GIVE UP A LONG
HOME RUN LIKE■■■■■■ THAT.
JON: SOWHAT HE'S TRYING TO DO IS
MAKE A PITCH LOOK LIKE IT'S A
KNEE-HIGH STRIKE.
HIGHEST PERCENTAGE OF PITCHES,
LOWER EDGE OF THE STRIKE ZONE --
IT'S TANAKA, THEN KERSHAW, THEN■
GREINKE.
BUT THAT'S WHERE HE OPERATES,
JUST RIGHT ON THE BOTTOM EDGES
AND USUALLY THE BOTTOM FALLS
OUT.
DAVID: IT'S RIGHT INTO HIS HAND
WITH THAT SPLIT.
EITHER FALLS OFF THE TABLE AND
LOOKS JUST LIKE A FASTBALL WHEN
YOU FACE HIM COMING OUT OF HIS
HAND.
HE'S GOT A TRUE FOUR-SEAMER SO
IT'S THE SAME ACTION, SAME
COMMITMENT TO THE PITCH WITH THE
ARM SPEED AND THE BOTTOM FALLS
OUT.
DAVID ORTIZ, WHEN WE FIRST FACED
O HIM■■■■ND YOU HAVEM
YOU'■G■DS■■■■■■■■+++KK■■ CHASIN■
STATISTICA■&YS THAT DON'TRE GUY■
HAVE GREAT COMMAND BUT FOR■Q■Q■Q
IT IS BY■/■/ DESIGN.
HE IS TRYING TO THROON
+ EDGES, ON THE MARGINS,■■ AND
■ WORKS FOR HIM.
■■■■■■■LLY GOOD A■'VE SEEN SOME0
CUTTERS THAT HE'LL THROW
BACKDOOR AWAY TO RIGHTIES.
JON: BACK TO THIRD, URSHELA.
THEY GET ONE.
THEY TURN IT.
GIO URSHELA IS REALLY GOOD AT
THIRD.
DAVID: NICE PLAY THERE.
DIDN'T PANIC, HARD-HIT BALL.
THAT'S THE TOUGHEST ONE.
OPPOSITE HITTER, LEFT-HANDED
HITTER TO THE LEFT SIDE OF THE
OUTFIELD, A LITTLE BIT OF A CUT
THERE.
URSHELA KNOCKS IT DOWN, STAYS
WITH IT.
THE KEY IS, HE DOESN'T PANIC.
NICE FIRM FEED, EASY FOR GLEYBER
TORRES TO TURN THAT BALL COMING
ACROSS THE BAG.
VERY NICE DEFENSE BYNKEES.■■R■■■
JON: 5-6■77"■7■■77■777■7■7777■■■
DAVIAS ALL OVER82O■=
PITCH.
SLIDER, BEEN THROWING A LOT■
BABY SLIDERS TO GET AHEAD.
THAT ONE JUST BACKED UP JUST A■■
HAIR.
WANTS TO HAVE T■■ ONE BACK, YOU
CAN TELL.GG
JON: AND THERE IT IS, TRYING TO
TEASE THE LOWER PART OF THE
ZONE.
DAVID: IF YOU EVER WANT TO KNOW
HOW NAST A PITCH IS, WATCH GARY
u■■■u■■■uu■■.
HE HAD TO FAT%%%
% DOWN.
THE BOTTOM% FELL OUT OF THAT
THING JUST OFF THE SAME■■■■LANEg
■UU■■LAST SLIDER.
IDN'T L!,■,
K-ZONE SAID IT DID■■uOT■ HIT.
ALTUVE HAS TIED IT UP WITH■uSO
ND ROSSI■■■■■ HERE IN
HOUSTON.
GOOD PITCH, SLIDER CLIPS THE
t t t ■■■■■ERO■■■■009 ■@úa■=&@&■
DAVID RACKLEY WRINGS UP CARLOS
CORREA.
You can't always believe
what you see.
Like if I,
hidden in the depths
of this soft taco,
you'd find Crunchy...
Melty...
Nachos.
For just one dollar.
Would you believe me?
Or are you just seeing things?
The new $1 Loaded Nacho Taco
from Taco Bell's Cravings
Value Menu.
Staying at Hampton
for a work trip.
When your
flight gets in late,
it's never too
early for coffee.
Oh no no no.
Your new boss
seems cool,
but she might not
be sweatpants cool.
Who is THAT
ready THIS early?
It's only 7 am.
Somebody help me.
Close call.
Not quite ready
to face the day?
That's why we're here
with free hot breakfast
and a warm welcome.
Book at Hampton.com for
our Price Match Guarantee.
Hampton by Hilton.
♪♪
Introducing freedom from the
bounds of convention...
Book at Hampton.com for
our Price Match Guarantee.
472 horses of V8
craftsmanship...
Zero to 60 in 3.96 seconds.
It's performance, born of
refinement.
The 2020 Lexus RC F Track
Edition and RC F.
Experience Amazing at your
Lexus dealer.
JON: BACK IN HOUSTON, BOOG
SCIAMBI, AARON DAVID ROSS.
AARON JUDGE MAKING HIS WAY TO
THE PLATE.
AARON JUDGE, THIRD MOST THROUGH
300 AT
HOW ABOUT MOST STRI
AND MOST WALKS, THOMAS, KELLER
AND JUDGE IS THIRD.■■■( ME■ AN ■
THROUGH HIS F■■■■F
AS WE MENTIONED, AN ABSOLUTE
STAR.
IT WILL BE GARDNER AND THEN
JUDGE AND THEN VOIT HERE IN THE
TOP HALFTHE FIFTH INNING.■hhhhM■
BRETT GARDNER -- HIS LAST TIME
UP.
THEY HAVE THE SHIFT.
THEY MOVE CORREA TO THE RIGHT OF
SECOND.
BREGMAN BACKS UP AND THEY PLAY A
PULL CONFIGURATION.
SHIFT AGAINST GARDNER.
WAS YELLING■ AT ■ HINCH AND I
THINK JOEADA, AS WELL.
SAYING,HAT AR GUYS DOING?
OU GOT TO PL■■■■■■ UP.
E K■
JON: YOU GOT TO PL ME ■■ X ■1
UP.I1■1I1
DAY■■ ■
PESTOLEN BH
WHAT OPEN TLD■  COVER.
ONE OF THE MOST SERIOUS BASEBALL
PLAYERS I'VE EVER BEEN AROUND.
HE IS IN THERE.
HE'S ALL BUSINESS WHEN HE'S IN
THERE.
FUNNY HIM YELLING IN THE DUGOUT.
YOU DON'T SEE HIM BREAK
CHARACTER TOO MUCH.■1
JON: HE GOT TO BE VERY CLOSE
WITH BRIAN MCCANN WHEN THE TWO
OF THEM WERE TOGETHER AT
TEAMMATES.
OVER TO FIRST.
GURRIEL TO VERLANDER.
AND ONE UP AND ONE DOWN.
1-1 GAME.
AARON JUDGE, A SEASON AGO, WE
TALKED ABOUT GETTING HIT BY
JAKOB JUNIS AND MISSING THE
TIME.
HERE'S THE YANKEES' RECORD WITH
HIM AND THE YANKEES RECORD
WITHOUT HIM.
RUNS PER GAME SUFFERED A BIT AND
SO DID THE O.P.S. AND IT JUST
STANDS TO REASON THAT A GUY THAT
WILL IMPACT BOTH THE ON BASE AND
THE SLUG, YOUR OFFENSE WOULDN'T
BE AS GOOD.
THERE'S AN ELEMENT OF IT, AS
WELL, DAVID, LIKE THAT SLIDER
DOWN AND AWAY, IT'S SUBTLE, BUT
HE'S COORDINATED, HE'S 6'7".
YOU BETTER MISS BECAUSE HE CAN
REACH SOME STUFF THAT THE
AVERAGE GUY CAN'T REACH.
DAVID: THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU HAVE TO KNOW WHERE HIS CHASE
ZONES ARE.
HE CAN GO GET SOME STUFF THAT
OTHER GUYS■ CAN'T, WHETHER IT'S
MANY REALLY ■ PLAYERS -- HE.■■■v
WANTS TO DRIVE, STAYS INSIDE THE
BALL AS GOOD AS ANYBODY.
HOW MANY PEOPLE CAN PLAY HOME
RUN DERBY OPPOSITE ■■■■■■■■■■■■■
WIN.
HEY, YOU'RE ONLY ALLOWED TO PLAY
ON THIS HALF OF THE FIELD AND
YOU CAN WIN IT.
NOT TOO MANY.
BIG STRONG GUY COVT OF
THE PLATE.
JON: HE'S DONE DIFFERENT THINGS
OFFENSIVELY.
HE'S GONE NO-STRIDE, TOE-TAP,
BIG LEG KICK AT■P■x TIM■2 H
HRIGHT FIELD.
THAT ONE BACK THERE.ON WAY, GON!
THE OPPOSITE @ WAY, THAT'S WHATE
DOES.
AARON JUDGE, I DON'T KNOW THAT
THERE'S ANYONE WITH HIS TYPE OF
PO)&2zZO■)ç)q)■4■■■ ■Qx WAITED,■
&EN THE YANKEES A 2-1
LEAD.
DAVID:■z8 AND HOUSE GAME
WITH HIM -- CAT-AND-MOUSE GAME
CAN HIM.
YOU GOT THE BREAKING BALL HERE,
DUMPER.
DER.THEY'V■F1@nLWNOT■s■RYRns÷g .
LEANS BACK.EP HE■@■@■p■p
THAT IS A NICE PIECE OF HITTING.
LEAN BACK ON HIM WE SAY, BABY.
THAT BALL IS CRUSHED.■■#■#■I■ñsy
JON: 103.8 MILES AN HOUR.
HIS FIRST TWO CAREER HITS
AGAINST JUSTIN VERLANDER, HE
CAME IN■ 0INGLE, AK
AND A HOMER.
DAVID: SUCH A PRESENCE IN THE
LINEUP.
I PLAYE A HOUSTON NATIVE
IN ADAM DUNN.
THIS GUY JUST HAD TO TOUCH IT.
JON: I THINK HE MIGHT BE HERE
TONIGHT.
DAVID: I HOPE SO.
JON: AARON BOONE SAID HE MIGHT
G TO■■■■■■■■@
I PLAYED WITH HIM IN
CINCINNATI.
THAT'S A BIG BOY.
HE BARRELED ANYTHING, SUCH AN
EASY SWING.
REMINDS ME A LOT OF JUDGE, WHEN
IT TOUCHES THE BARREL, IT
EXPLODES.
JON: AARON BOONE AND ADAM DUNN
PLAYED TOGETHER IN CINCINNATI.
JUDGE, WHOSE SEASON --
INJURY-PLAGUED A SEASON AGO, HIT
27 HOME RUNS.
THIS TO CENTER FIELD.
VOIT FLIES TO SPRINGER.
WE'VE SHOWED YOU THIS BEFORE,
OUR HOME RUN TRACKER.
LAUNCH ANGLE, IDEALLY YOU'RE
LOOKING FOR SOMEWHERE BETWEEN
LIKE 23 AND 30%, THE APEX TOP
HEIGHT AT 63 FEET.
ONLY WENT 346 FEET BUT THE EXIT
VELO AROUND 100 AND THAT GUY
HITS BULLETS.■■■
AARON JUDGE, HOME RUN NUMBER
THREE.
YANKEES WHO LED THE MAJORS IN
HOMERS HIT LAST YEAR, SET A
MAJOR LEAGUE RECORD.
VERLANDER DEALS.
AARON BOONE KNOWS WHAT THEY'VE
GOT.
HE'S GOT A TEAM THAT WHEN
THEY'RE HEALTHY, THEY'LL HOMER
AGAIN.
THEY'LL STR OUT SOME.
NOT AN ABNORMAL AMOUNT.
I WOULD SAY SLIGHTLY ABOVE
AVERAGE.
THEY'RE GOING TO WALK, AS WELL,
AND THEY'RE GOING TO SCORE.
DAVID: IT'S NOT ONE OF THOSE
HOME RUN HITTING TEAMS THAT ARE
FREE SWINGING.
THEY GIVE YOU PNAL
■/S.
THEY HAVE A GAME PLAN AND WILL
TURN IT OVER TO THE NEXT GUY.
THEY HAVE A LOT OF■■THAT
SEEM TO STEP UP IN BIG
SITUATIONS.
THEY ALL LIKE THAT MOMENT.
A POISED, PROFESSIONAL LINEUP.
JON: BOUNCE TO SHORT.
BACKHANDED BY CORREA.
STRONG THROW TO FIRST IN TIME.
THAT'S THE INNING.■ HEAD TOí1qOE
xExE
FIFTH ■?>?>9>9>9>9>9>9>9>■ç>y J.
ó
I'm off to collegeMMworr' retir.
Don't worry.
Voya helps them to and through
retirement...
dealing with today's expenses
...while helping plan,
invest and the
future
So they'll be okay?
I think they'll be fine.
Voya. Helping you to
and through retirement.
MOVING?
THAT'S HARDER NOW BECAUSE
OF PSORIATIC ARTHRITIS.
BUT YOU'RE STILL MOVED
BY MOMENTS LIKE THIS.
DON'T LET PSORIATIC
ARTHRITIS TAKE THEM AWAY.
TALTZ REDUCES JOINT
PAIN AND STIFFNESS
LPS STOP THE
PROGRESSION OF JOINT DAMAGE.
FOR PEOPLE WITH
MODERATE TO
SEVERE PSORIASIS,
90% SAW SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT.
TALTZ EVEN GIVES YOU A CHANCE
AT COMPLETELY
CLEAR SKIN.
DON'T USE IF YOU'RE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING, YOU SHOULD
BE CHECKED FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR
ABILITY TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU
HAVE AN INFECTION, SYMPTOMS,
OR RECEIVED A
VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INCLUDING WORSENING OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
FOR ALL THE THINGS
THAT MOVE YOU.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
♪ ♪
(nature, ambient sounds, birds■■
in flight, running water)
(car horn - barely audible)
(car horn - increasing in volume
and intensity)
(car horn - loud)
Jane, this is Jim from OnStar.
I've contacted help
and they're on their way.
O.K.
Don't worry I'm going to stay
with you until help arrives.
Thank you.
That deer, it just, just came
out of nowhere.
JON: THE MLB BALLPLAYER APP WILL
COM YOUR NEXT VISIT TO YOUR
FAVORI■ BALLPARK.
DOWNLOAD THE MLB BALLPARK APP
TODAY.
ROCKET TO RIGHT OFF THE BAT OF
YULI GURRIEL.
BACK TO THE STUDIO, KEVIN
CONNORS.
KEVIN: CONCERN IN ST. LOUIS.
DODGERS-CARDINALS.
HYUN-JIN RYU ON THE MOUND.
SOMETHING DIDN'T FEEL RIGHT.
TRAINERS CAME OUT.
HE WAS■■■■vUT OF THE% GAME.
HE MISSED THREE MONTHS WITH A
GROIN INJURY A SEASON AGO.
MEANTIME IN KANSAS CITY, ALEX
GORDON, R.B.I. SINGLE.
TWO IN THE FIRST FOR THE ROYALS,
WHIT MERRIFIELD HAS EXTENDED HIS
HIT STREAK TO 29 GAMES.
JON: THE THE RYU INJURY IS SCARY
FOR THE DODGERS.
THEY BUILD THEIR ROSTER ONE
THROUGH 40 AND THEY'RE READY
WITH THEIR DEPTH WHETHER YOU'RE
TALKING URIAS OR STRIPLING.
THE THING WITH RYU, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE INJURY WAS.
HE BASICALLY MISSED TWO FULL
YEARS WITH A SHOULDER INJURY SO
IT'S BEEN A TOUGH GO FOR HIM.
DAVID: DIDN'T L WAS TOO
CONCERNED WALK■d■d■d■d■& AT HISE
T.E IT WAS A■;■;■;■;■;Q7y7■7■7■.
THEY'VE DEALT WITH INJURIES ON
THAT STAFF.
JON: I'M GOING TO SIT HERE AND
SAY I THINK THE DODGERS ARE
GOING TO BE FINE.
DAVID: SEEMS LIKE THEY SCORE 10
A NIGHT.
JON: THERE'S ALSO THE ELEMENT,
THEY BUILT THEIR ROSTER IN A
WAY -- THEY'VE USED -- WE SHOWED
THE STAT WITH THE DODGERS.
ALL FOUR YEARS UNDERREW
FRIEDMAN, THEY'VE USED AT LEAST
LAYERS AND IN THE 125 YEARS
OF THAT FRANCHISE PRIOR, THEY
HAD DONE IT TWICE.
IVELY ARE USING LOTS OF
PLAYERS.
DAVID: THE SPEECH DAVE ROBERTS
GAVE THOSE GUYS IN SPRING
TRAINING, HEY, LOOK, THIS IS
AT WE DO, WE USE EVERYBODY SO
EXPECT TO BE UP HERE.
WE'RE GOING TO USE YOU.
I DON'T CARE WHAT LEVEL WE'RE
AT, IF YOU BELONG HERE, WE WILL
FIND A SPOT FOR YOU.
INJURIES HAPPEN AND WE NEED
EVERYBODY IN THE ORGANIZATION ON
THAT 40-MAN ROSTER.
JON: HERE'S TYLER WHITE.
WITH TWO DOWN.
THIS GUY'S A GOOD HITTER.
HE'S IMPROVED DEFENSIVELY.
33RD ROUND PICK IN 2013 OUT OF
WESTERN CAROLINA.
THEY LIKE THE STRIKE ZONE
SCROLL, GOOD ON BASE SKILLS AND
THE SLUG.
CENTER FIELD, GARDNER IS RIGHT
THERE.
THEY GO 1-2-3 ON EIGHT PITCHES.
New lower price.
Wow. That's a lot
of asparagus.
Yeah, you said get
a bunch of asparagus.
Oh, you...
bunch.
I... thought you kinda...
Alrighty, you guys are
almost all set.
bunch.
Great!
Sounds good!
Honey, while you finish up here,
I'll grab us
some coffee.
Ok.
♪ ♪
(music stops)
Ready to go?
But... I...
♪ ♪
Getting a Volkswagen during the
Sign Then Drive Event.
It's almost that easy.■
With practically just your
signature,
you can get a 2019 Volkswagen
Jetta
for zero down, zero deposit,
zero first month's payment,
and zero due at signing.
JON: YANKS OFF TO A 5-4 START.
ACE IN THE HOLE WITH SEVERINO ON
THE SHELF AND DOUBLE WHAMMY,
BETANCES, SON OF A PITCH.
IS THERE A DOCTOR IN THE HOUSE.
THEY HAVE SOME PRETTY CLEVER
HEADLINE WRITERS.
I CAN STILL REMEMBER THE YANKS,
PLAYING THE WHITE SOX, PICKING
UP THE BACK PAGE OF THE "POST"
AND THEY HAD BEEN SWEPT THREE IN
A ROW AND IT JUST SAID,
"STINKY."
DAVID: THEY'VE ALWAYS GOT THEM
LAID OUT.
YOU GO TO THE VISITING
CLUBHOUSE, YOU COME TO TOWN,
THEY'VE GOT THEM ALL LAID OUT IN
THE CLUBHOUSE.
"THE POST," "THE TIMES."
JON: NOT "THE TIMES".
"THE POST" AND THE NEWS, THE
DESSERT OF NEWSPAPERS.
TOWARDS RIGHT CENTER.
SPRINGER DIDN'T SEE IT BUT
REDDICK DID.
ROSSI, I'M GOING TO READ PROMO
FOUR.
"SPORTSCENTER" COMING UP NEXT
WITH KENNY MAYNE AND ZUBIN
MEHENTI.
THEY'LL HAVE LIVE POSTGAME
REACTION AND CELEBRATION FROM
THE NCAA TITLE GAME.
WHY JAMES HARDEN IS UNGUARDABLE
AND INSIDE THE START OF THE
YANKEES SEASON ON "SPORTSCENTER"
COMING UP NEXT ON ESPN.
NICE NIGHT.
ROOF IS OPEN HERE A MINUTE MAID
PARK.
AND THE FIRST OFFERING IS A
STRIKE TO GREG BIRD.
BACK TO THE STUDIO, KEVIN
CONNORS.
KEVIN: THIS IS NOTHING PERSONAL
HERE.
I'M SURE CHRIS DAVIS IS A SWELL
GUY BUT THIS AT-BAT COULD BE
MAJOR LEAGUE HISTORY.
0-46 AND HE GOES HITLESS HERE,
IT IS HISTORY AND THERE YOU HAVE
IT.
GAVE IT A RIDE BUT THAT'S 0 FOR
HIS LAST 47 SO SOMEWHERE, BOOG,
EUGENIO VALEZ IS POPPING THE
CHAMPAGNE TONIGHT.
DAVID: THOSE ARE THREE LINE
DRIVES, TOO.
TWO OPPO, ONE TO RIGHT.
THAT STINKS.
SORRY, CHRIS DAVIS.
I FEEL BAD FOR YOU, BUDDY.■
JON: LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION.
IF YOUE 0-47 AND I WLIKE,
ROSSI, THOSE WERE THREE
LINE DRIVES TO LEFT FIELD.
YOU KNOW, THAT SHOULD FEEL GOOD.
HOW WOULD THAT WORK OUT FOR ME?
DAVID: IF I WAS CHRIS DAVIS I'D
BE LIKE, YEAH, SAVE IT, BOOG,
AND I'M RICH, BY THE WAY.
I'M REALLY RICH.
JON: YOUR LONGEST 0-FER WAS
0-21.
DAVID: THANKS FOR BRINGING IT
UP.
WHAT WAS THE DATE ON THAT?
JON: 2005.
DAVID: JUST A SHELL OF A MAN.
JON: IF IT MAKES YOU FEEL ANY
BETTER, I AVE GUESSED
LONGER THAN THAT.
EVEN-GAME STRETCH FOR
ME IS LIKE THREE MONTHS.
JON: INTO THE GAP LEFT CENTER,
BANGS UP AGAINST THE WALL.
D.J. LEMAHIEU WITH A TWO-OUT
DOUBLE.
DAVID: REALLY NICE SWING HERE BY
D.J.
GOT A SLIDER, JUST STAYS IN THE
THAT IS RIGHT INTO THAT BARREL.■
HEAD DOWN, BACK SIDE,■÷ SO EARLL
TO THE RIGHT SIDE.
THAT SLIDER REALLY SPEEDS UP HIS
BAT AND THAT'S A■ LINE DRIVE IN■
■ ■Cç4■ ■■■■■w■w■w■w■■w■w■w■■■■
WITH TWO OUTS.
JON: YANKEES UP UP BY A RUN.
HERE'Sh FRA
FRAZIER 1-2 WITH A SINGLE AND A
STRIKE.
OFF TO A GOOD START.
LAST YEAR, INJURY PLAGUED
SEASON, HAND, DEALT WITH A
CONCUSSION ISSUE.
HE CAN RUN AND HE'S GOT SOME
THUMP IN HIS BAT.
DEALING WITH A TOUGH CUSTOMER IN
JUSTIN VERLANDER, THE VETERAN,
ONE OF THE TOP STRIKEOUT
PITCHERS IN THE SPORT.
HE'S UP OVER 100 PITCHES, AND SO
WILL HAR RIGHT-HANDER, UP
AND GETTING LOOSE.
A.J. HINCH, FIGURE THINGS OUT.
VERLANDER, WHO WAS ACQUIRED
RIGHT AT THE END OF JULY IN
2017, HE WAS SENSATIONAL FOR
THEM.
HAMMERED LEFT FIELD TOWARDS THE
CRAWFORD BOX SEATS AND THAT
ONE'S OFF THE TOP OF THE WALL.
RACING AROUND AND INTO TO SCORE
IS LEMAHIEU, A ROCKET OFF THE
BAT OF CLINT FRAZIER, JUST
MISSED GETTING OUT.
THE YANKEES LEAD 3-1.
■dUd■d■d■d■■d■d■F■■■■■■■■ FOOT n
LOOKA CLOSE THIS BALL IS TO
GOING OUT.))■@ @ ■8■
JUST OFF THAT UNITED AIRLINES
SIGN.
■■ó)ó)■17@7@■@;@;@ BASE RUNNINGO
STAY AT FIRST.
MOST GUYS GET EXCITED AND WOULD
HAVE BEEN THROWN OUT AT SECOND.
JON: CORRECT ON THING, FOR
VERLANDER IN 1917, IT WAS END OF
AUGUST THAT THEY MADE THAT DEAL.
IT WAS RIGHT THERE BEFORE
SEPTEMBER AND HE MADE THE FIVE
STARTS DOWN THE STRETCH AND
BRILLIANT INTO THE POSTSEASON,
GREAT LAST YEAR.
HE'S BEEN OFF THE CHARTS AS AN
ASTRO.
DAVID: THAT THE
WO9>ôô■;LY LOOKAT IT.■;?■■)■)?■>
JON: 41 STARTS WITH THE ASTROS
COMING INTO TONIGHT AND 2.40
E.R.A., A HUGE PART OF THAT
WORLD CHAMPIONSHIP BANNER IN
LEFT CENTER FIE■%■ ñ,ñ=■]■■
■ñO?O■■■■■8-O■>.
D: USING THAT P MORE
WE■■ KNEW HE'S
THAT INSEASON AND SPRING
TRAINING, THROWING A LOTORE
CHANGEUPS.
CONSTANTLY TRYING TO EVOLVE.
JON: LAST YEAR, THE ENTIRE YEAR
HE THREW AROUND 53 OF THEM AND
HE'SÑ>Ñ■>■L■■W■■?g■g■O■÷■■C■■áGE
x;■?:I■Ió#L>■■■■W IN TERMS OFqqq
TOTAL FOR THE SEASON.SAIDT, I TE
OPEb8■8■8■)i8■)■)■)■)■)9)9)■)9)L
TRYING TO EVOLVE.
DAVID: I TALKED TO BRANTLEY AND
SPRINGER AND CORREA AND THEY
SAID THEY SEE MORE RIGHT ON
RIGHT" AND LEFT ON RIGHT
CHANGEUPS THAN THEY'VE EVER SEEN
IN HIS CAREER.
THE PITCHES ARE EVOLVING.
WHEN I WAS COMING UP, WE WERE
TAUGHT NOT TO THROW -- IF YOU
THREW I OPPOSITE1ER,
07 @#■■HT PITCH
THRO A LEFT-HANDED
HITTER.
ANY MORE, THAT'S NOT THE RULE.
GUYS WILL THROW ANY PITCH ANY
TIME.
JON: FALLING BEHIND HERE, 3-1.
BACK OUR WAY.
DAVID: THIS GUY HAS BEEN TAKING
PICTURES WITH HIS SON IN FRONT
OF US ALL NIGHT.
SO EXCITED.
LITTLE BABY BOY HAS AN ASTROS
UNI ON, SO EXCITED TO BE HERE
AND THE FOUL BALL CAME RIGHT TO
HIM.
HOW COOL THAT?
THAT'S KARMA RIGHT HERE.
JON: I LOVE THE GRUNT.
VERLANDER GETS THE STRIKEOUT IN
WHAT IS LIKELY HIS FINAL PITCH
OF THE NIGHT AT 96 MILES AN
HOUR.
FRAZIER HELPS THE YANKEES ADD
ON, 3-1, NEW YORK.
y■&aa
r our frt
with giveaways, crafts,
an egg hunt,
and a free picture
with the Easter Bunny.
Go online to learn more.
Your Adventure Starts Here
GATORADE ZERO.
ALL THE ELECTROLYTES.
ZERO SUGAR.
♪♪
GET MORE OUT OF ZERO.
Staying at Hampton
for a work trip.
When your
flight gets in late,
it's never too
early for coffee.
Oh no no no.
Your new boss
seems cool,
but she might not
be sweatpants cool.
Who is THAT
ready THIS early?
It's only 7 am.
Somebody help me.
Close call.
Not quite ready
to face the day?
That's why we're here
with free hot breakfast
and a warm welcome.
Book at Hampton.com for
our Price Match Guarantee.
Hampton by Hilton.
Book at Hampton.com for
our Price Match Guarantee.
♪ ♪
RUN WITH US.
On a John Deere
X300 Series
Because seasons may change...
♪ ♪
...but true character doesn't.
Wow, you've outdone
lf this time.
Hey, what're neighbors for?
It's beautiful.
Nothing Runs Like A Deere™.
RUN WITH US.
300 on X330 and X350
At participating John Deere
dealers.
Experience the style,
craftsmanship and technology
that have made the RX
the leading luxury
SUV of all time.
Lease the 2019 RX 350 for
$409 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
KEVIN: THE BALL IS FLYING OUT OF
THE PARK IN PHILLY TONIGHT.
SUZUKI, HERRARA AND NOW RHYS
SKINS, HIS FOURTH OF THE YEAR.
THIR G■uOME
RUN.
YOU CAN SEE THAT RIúaW ON
ESPN+.
MEANTIME, BRAVES-ROCKIES, RONALD
ACUNA JR., OPPO BOPPO OFF KYLE■%
FREELAND.
HE DESTROYS THAT ONE.
444 FEET.
BRAVES LEAD THE ROCKIES IN THE
BOTTOM OF THE FIRST.
AND DANIEL VOGELBACH, HITTING .
.500 ON THE YEAR, BOOG.
JON: I LIKE HIS BODY.
HE'S GOT THAT STOCKY --
DAVID: HE'S EX-CUB.
HE WAS WITH THE CUBBIES WHEN I
WAS PLAYING.
SHORT ARMS.
AND H■NG FOR THE FENCESo@ííí■■■N
SHARP.
GIVEN UP A HOME RUN TO ALTUVE.
THAT'S ONE OF TWO HITS.
THE OTHER, LINE DRIVE SINGLE OFF
THE BAT OF ALEX BREGMAN.
THIS WILL BE PITCH NUMBER 63.
DAVID: GARY SANCHEZ, HIGH
FASTBALL TARGET■pCKaadadada a a8
HIM.o■■ñ[ç■■g■■
URSHELA.THE GROUND.
DOWN INTO THE LEFT FIELD CORNER.
FRAZIER WILL TRY TO DIG IT OUT.
CHIRINOS HAS A DOUBLE.
DAVID: GETTING THAT LEADOFF GUY
ON IS SO IMPORTANT.■f■■
ROBINSON CHIRINOS TAKES THAT■■ff
SPLIT.
SINKING DOWN AND IN TO HIM.
KEEPS HIS HANDS INSIDE, KEEPS IT
FAIR DOWN THE LEFT FIELD LINE,
PAST URSHELA.
LEADOFF DOUBLE.
TOP OF THE LINEUP COMING UP FOR
THE ASTROS.
JON: A MAN IN SCORING POSITION.
ASTROS, EARLY IN THE SEASON,
SITUATIONAL HITTING HAS NOT BEEN
GREAT.
SPRINGER WOULDN'T BITE.
NOW 2-0.
DAVID: WHEN THESE RALLIES START,
IT'S HARD TO BE PATIENT.
YOU SEE SPRINGER HERE.
THEY WANT TO■aWaWaWaIT■.
YOU HAVE TO BE THE MOST PATIENT
AGAINST TANAKA.
JON: ALTUVE LURKING IN THE
ON-DECK CIRCLE AND TANAKA WILL
STEP OFF.
MASAHIRO TANAKA, 30 YEARS OLD.
AGAIN, TRYING TO TEASE THAT
STRIKE ZONE.
CHIRINOS AT SECOND.
3-0 TO SPRINGER.
TANAKA -- THAT CLIPS THE CORNER.
DAVID: YOU SEE WHAT GREAT
COMMAND HE HAS WITH THIS CUTTER
HE THROWS, JUST OUTSIDE.
GENEROUS CALL, 3-0.
JON: IT DID NOT CLIP THE BLOCK
OF CHEESE.
YANKS STARTING TO GET ACTIVITY
IN THE PEN WITH HOLDER UP.
STRIKE TWO.
DAVID: THERE'S A TWO-SEAMER
COMING BACK.
NOW YOU'RE IN BETWEEN, IF YOU'RE
SPRINGER.
SAW THREE CUTTERS FOR A BALL AND
THEN A BORDER MINE CUTTER FOR A
STRIKE AND THEN THE TWO-SEAMER
COMING BACK.
I WOULD BET THE HOUSE ON A
SPLIT-FINGER RIGHT NOW.
JON: THAT'S MIDDLE-MIDDLE.
DAVID: IF WE'RE BETTING, I'M ALL
IN ON THE SPLIT-FINGER.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING?
JON: YOU'RE THE ANALYST, LET'S
GO.
I'M WITH DAVID RO
DAVI■nm 95.
JON: AND K-ZONE SAID IT GOT THE
CORNER.
DAVID: NICE SEQUENCE TO COME
BACK THERE BY TANAKA.
THAT BALL WAS BORDERLINE STRIKE
DID.
THAT GET ANY CHEESE?
I SEE A LITTLE SLIVER.
THAT'S LIKE THE CHEESE THEY
JUST A LITTLE■)■)■@úúhbhb■8■8■8■
n■zz
JON: MEETING ON THE MOUND AND WE
HAVE A MOMENT TO LOOK AT
POWERFUL STUFF BROUGHT TO YOU BY
CONSTANT CONTACT.
LOTS OF CONTACT RIGHT THERE.
HOW ABOUT ALMOSTT OFF
THE BAT OF JOSE ALTUVE.
AND FOR ALTUVE, HOME RUN NUMBER
TWO, TIED THE GAME 1-1.
THE YANKEES HAVE SCORED TWICE
SINCE AND LEAD IT 3-1.c]oyYáM■y■
ANDVV THERE■■#■■#■E■&C÷■]■zES PG
■pRRY?;■L
C ■  ROTHSCHILD, ONE OF
THE BEST IN THE GAME.
HOLDER, THE RIGHT-HANDER,
CONTINUES TO GET LOOSE.
JONATHAN HOLDER THROWING.
BULLPEN COACH TO HIS RIGHT.
ANOTHER GIANT MAN.
IT'S CHIRINOS AT SECOND.
SPRINGER AT FIRST AND NOBODY
OUT.
ALTUVE, A GUY THAT LIKES THAT
FIRST PITCH.
■■■OFF THE PLATE HESWING.
IS THERE.
NICE THROW FROM TANAKA, KNOWING
HE'S READY TO HIT.
REALLY FEEDING OFF THE ENERGY OF
THE CROWD.
STILL GOT TO MAKE HIM COME TO
JON: PERCENTAGE OF PLATE
APPEARANCES LASTING ONE PITCH,
GURRIEL BEHIND■ ALEDMYS DIAZ.
SANCHEZ HELD IT FOR THAT EXTRA
SECOND.
LOOKED LIKE DAVID RACKLEY WAS
SAYING THAT PITCH WAS OUTSIDE.
DAVID: TANAKA ASKED.
I THINK HE WANTED THAT PITCH.
THAT'S ONE OF THEOUGHER
PITCHES TO CATCH, THAT
SPLIT-FINGER, NOT KNOWING WHERE
IT'S GOING.
YOU SAW HIM THROW THAT BACKDOOR
RIGHT THERE.
JON: THAT CATCHES THE CORNER.
DAVID, REALLY QUICKLY, IT FEELS
LIKE IT WAS A PITCH THAT WAS IN
VOGUE FOR A WHILE WITH ROGER
CRAIG.
TAKE ANOTHER LOOK.
GOT THE CHEESE.
DAVID: THAT'S A NICE PITCH.
JON: DID YOU CATCH A LOT OF
SPLITTERS?
THERE AREN'T A TON OF THEM OUT
THERE RIGHT NOW.
DAVID: I CAME UP CATCHING NOMO
WHO WAS ONE OF THE BEST IN THE
BUS AND■Wú1ú1ú1ú1ú1ú1■a;uqaqa■aT
CONTROL WITH HIS■■■ÑÑÑÑ■u■u■Ñ■Ñ,
ONE OF THE BEST CLOSERS I'VE
EVER CAUGHT.
THE YEAR HE HAD IN BOSTON WAS
AMAZING.
HIS SPLIT-FINGER REMINDS ME A
LOT OF WHAT TANAKA IS DOING
TODAY,G THAT THING
BACKDOOR AND LETTING IT BRING
IT, ALMOST LIKE A TWO-SEAMER.
JON: TWO ON, NOBODY OUT.
1-2.
A LITTLE ROLLER, SAFE AT FIRST.
COMINGd BACK FROM THAT OFFSEASON
KNEE SURGERY, NOT RUNNING LIKE
HE ONCE DID.
THE HOPE IS THAT HE WILL GET
BACK THERE.
DAVID: BANG-BANG HERE.
GETS A NICE ROLLER FROM ALTUVE
■8■, TURN.TCH.
LEMAHIEU TOO FAST.
I THINK ALTUVE GONNA BE SAFE.
HE'LL GET DOWN THAT LINE EVEN
WITH THE KNEE SURGERY.
YOU GET THAT FRONEADING
OUT, A Lr■O EXTRA M■Cv■
COMING OUT OF THE BOX.
JOSE NEEDED THAT TO BE SAFE.
JON: TWO ON, ONE OUT.■=■=■=■=
AND A DANGEROUS MAN AT THE DISH.
25 YEARS OLD, AN ALL-STAR AND
THE ALL-STAR GAME M.V.P. LAST
YEAR IN WASHINGTON, D.C., ALEX
BREGMAN.
THE OTHER THING WE TALKED ABOUT
AS FAR AS BREGMAN, HE'S GOT THAT
CONFIDENCE AND HE'S A GOOD
CLUBHOUSE GUY.
HE'S ONE OF THOSE GUYS, HE'S
GONE OUT OF HIS WAY TO LEARN
SPANISH.■,■,
AND HE'S ONE OF THOSE UNITERS,
ONE OF THOSE GUYS THAT BRINGS
EVERYBODY TOGETHER.
TYPICALLY IN THIS SPORT IT'S
BEEN THE LATIN GUYS HAVE BEEN
FORCED TO LEARN ENGLISH AND HIS
THING WAS, OK, WELL MAYBE I NEED
TO TAKE A STEP THAT DIRECTION
AND LEARN SPANISH.
AND HE PLAYS IN AN INFIELD WHERE
SPANISH IS THE FIRST LANGUAGE OF
CORREA, OF ALTUVE AND GURRIEL.
DAVID: THAT'S GREAT AWAREF
HIS SURROUNDINGS, ANOTHER REASON
WHY HE'S A BASEBALL RAT.
JON: THE ASTROS, WITH MEN IN
SCORING POSITION, .162, GO
FIGURE, 29TH OUT OF 30 TEAMS.
THEY'VE BEEN GETTING ON BASE,
THEY'VE BEEN SLUGGING.
I WAS ASKING A.J. HINCH, WHAT'S
THE DEAL, WHY HAVEN'T YOU GUYS
SCORED?
AND HE SAID IT'S THE SITUATIONA.
■çç IS, IF THEY'RE THI IN
THE LE■■■■■■■ IN ON BASE AND FOH
IN SLUGGING BY JUNE, I THINK THE
RUNS PER GAME WILL WORK ITSELF
OUT.
DAVID: THEY'LL BE JUST FINE.
JON: 1-1.
POPPED UP AND IT'S JUDGE COMING
DOWN.
HE MAKES THE CATCH.
DAVID: SOME OF THE KEYS FOR ME,
WITH GUYS IN SCORING POSITION,
GOT TO THINK SMALL.
NICE PITCH BY TANAKA.
HE'S MASTERED THE SLIDER ON THE
OUTSIDE PART OF THE PLATE TO THE
RIGHT-HANDED HITTER.
HE KEEPS IT RIGHT ON THE EDGE OF
THE STRIKEYOU REACH
FOR IT AS HE'S GOT THAT
CROSS-BODY DELIVERY.
BREGMAN JUST PULLS OFF IT ENOU
TO FLY OUT TO RIGHT.
WITH JUDGE'S ARM, YOU'RE NOT
TESTING THAT THING FROM THIRD.
JON: AARON JUDGE, ONE OF THE
BETTER THROWING ARMS OUT THERE.
DAVID: I REALLY I THINK THAT
SITUATIONAL HITTING, HITTING
WITH RUNNERS IN SCORING
POSITION, WE LOVE A BIG NUMBER.
IF WE CAN THINK SMALL, BASE HIT,
STAY UP THE■MALL
DETAILS -- AS I'VE GOTTEN OUT OF
THE GAME, IT'S EVEN MORE  CLEAR4
JON: HIT SOFTLY.
LEMAHIEU■?? IS THERE.
TANAKA, REALLY GOOD WORK
PITCHING OUT OF THAT JAM.
ASTROS LEAVE A COUPLE.
Ñ ■>■■%■■
JON: WELCOME BACK TO MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL ON ESPN.
OUR TELECAST TONIGHT PRESENTED
BY USAA.
FOLKS, PLAY BALL IS MLB'S
INITIATIVE TO INSPIRE ALL
FORMATION OF BASEBALL AND
SOFTBALL PARTICIPATION, MAKING
PLAYTUNITIES AVAILABLE AND
FUN FOR EVERYONE.
TO FIND A YOUTH ORGANIZATION
NEAR YOU, GO TO PLAYBALL.ORG.
BACK AT MINUTE MAID PARK, JON
SCIAMBI AND DAVID ROSS.
THE ROOF IS OPEN.
IF YOU'RE FROM THE MIDWEST, THE
ROOF.
TOP SEVEN, YANKEES UP 3-1.
GARDNER AT THE DISH.
JUSTIN VERLANDER DONE FOR THE
NIGHT.
SIX INNINGS, SEVEN HITS, THREE
RUNS, ALL EARNED.
SIX PUNCH-OUTS, A COUPLE OF
WALKS, 111 PITCHES.
WHAT DID YOU THINK?
DAVID: I THOUGHT HE THREW WELL.
IT WAS A TOUGH LINEUP.
THE BIG BOYS CONNECTED FOR SOME
HOMERS.
JON: HARRIS, THREE APPEARANCES.
LAST YEAR WASN'T A GREAT YEAR
FOR WILL HARRIS.
BUT, ROSSI, DIGEST THIS FOR ONE
SECOND.
15, 16 AND 17 FOR WILL HARRIS,
180 APPEARANCES, 180 1/3
INNINGS, 2.3 E.R.A. AND BETTER
THAN A STRIKEOUT AN INNING.
WHEN>yVERSE?■% VOLATILE.
HE■EENREALLY G■,■,■■>■T■■>■L>>>;
>>>> LIKES AND HAS ■/:/■/■:/
OFNCE WHEN HE'S ON THE
MOUND.
GOT THAT CUT FASTBALL, LIKES TO
PITCH IN THE ZONE.
HAS A NICE 12-6 BREAKING BALL,
ATTACKING HITTERS COMING RIGHT
AT HIM.
JON: HIT HIGH, GURRIEL, GLOVE
SAVE AND I■■■■■■%■%■%■■v■■■■■■■S
FIRST.
HERE THE JUDGE.
WE TAKE A LOOK TONIGHT'S
TRNTT■ BROUGHT TO YOU
BY LA QUINTA BY WINDHAM.
BANG, THE OTHER WAY.
FASTBALL UP AND AWAY AND HE
BLOCKED IT OVER THE RIGHT FIELD
WALL.
THAT'S THE POWER THAT GUY HAS.
FOR AARON JUDGE,  THIRDq%■■q%■ .
AND THE YANKEES LED 2-1.
FRAZIER, R.B.I. SINGLE TO MAKE
IT 3-1 AND THAT'S WHERE WE ARE.
HOW ABOUT, INTO THAT AGAINST
JUSTIN VERLANDER 0-13, SEVEN
PUNCHIES, AS THE KIDS SAY.
TONIGHT, 2-2, SOLO HOMER AND A
WALK.
DAVID: THAT'S THE STUFF I LIKE
TO, AND WALKING UP TOMORROW, HOW
MUCH HOMEWORK DID YOU DO OFF
VERLANDER?
MORE THAN NORMAL?
JUST WATCH YOUR AT-BAT?
WHEN YOU'RE 0-13 WITH SEVEN
PUNCHIES, IT'S A TOUGH GO TO
HAVE CONFIDENCE AND THAT BROKEN
BAT SINGLE IN THE FIRST --
JON: THAT'S TO RIGHT BUT SLICED
FOUL.
DAVID: HE'S GOT ALMOST A SMALL
GUY SWING, HOW HE STAYS INSIDE
THE BALL.ñ#■#
ATTACKS THE BALL LIKE A■>■■■■■■■
HITTER, AT SUCH A BIG SIZE.
HE'S TRYING TO TOUCH THAT THING
TO RIGHT.GXN,■øgs'■■vuOuOuO]■O■I
THE ZONE, SAUCE,
SPEED HIM UP AND  LEFT.■D
JON: WOULDN'T BITE ON A 1-2.
DABER ONE SELLING
JERSEY, RIGHT, UNTIL THIS YEAR?X
JON: YEAH, NOW IT'S BRYCE
HARPER.
DAVID: RAN OUT OF "R'S," I
HEARD.
TO MAKE THE BRYCE HARPER JERSEY.
JON: I THOUGHT THAT I READ IN
TERMS OF DAY ONE, THAT HARPER
PHILLY JERSEYS SOLD MORE THAN
LEBRON LAKER JERSEYS, THE FIRST
DAY THAT HE SIGNED, ON A 24-HOUR
TRACKING.
AND■DN'T■&■ CLOSE■ THAT PITCH.
ONE OUT, MAN ABOARD.
KEVIN: UPDATE ON
MARINERS-ROYALS.
KING FELIX HAS LEFT THE GAME
WITH A VIRUS-LIKE SYMPTOMS.
IT'S 4-2.
THE MARINERS HAVE HOMERED IN
EVERY GAME THIS SEASON.
DODGERS-CARDINALS, COREY SEAGER
DELIVERING AN R.B.I. SINGLE MADE
IT 3-2.
STILL 14 SHY OF TEAM LEADER CODY
BELLINGER.
JON: DODGERS KEEP ON SCORING.
DAVID: THAT'S A TEAM WE TALK
ABOUT COMMANDING THE STRIKE
ZONE.
THAT'S A TEAM THAT DOES A
PHENOMENAL JOB A~■krJk
■ ■E
E■E0E■E■E#@#@■@#@
VOIT, R.B.I. SINGLE SANDWICHED
BETWEEN A STRIKEOUT AND THE
FLY-OUT.
SO LUKE VOIT, LAST 100 BATTED
BALLS.
A PRETTY SEVERE PULL TENDENCY
AND THEY PLAY HIM ACCORDINGLY.
YOU'RE TALKING 87% OF HIS BATTED
BALLS 200 FEET OR LEFT ARE GOING
LEFT OF SECOND1g■é■@ GOINGO FACL
VOIT SWINGS AND MISSES,
STRIKEOUT, TWO AWAY.r÷■÷r÷r÷r÷p■
■■uuuuu■yuuuuu■7ú7ú7ú■7ú
>ú>ú>ú>ú>ú>ú>ú>úrp■p>ú>ú>ú>ú>ú>ú
TEAMMATES, WHATEVER IT IS, THAT
HE'S DOING IN THERE.
THAT'S A RARITY, FOR SURE.
JON: TALKING WITH COLLIN MCHUGH
WHO WILL JOIN US DURING THE
BROADCAST TOMORROW NIGHT.
THERE'S COLLIN.
HE'S GOT A GREATT, T
BYTHE WAY.
THE 12-6 PODCA■■Q%@■c■■■■Ce■■■■.
HAD SEAN DOOLITTE
NATIONALS ON.
IT IS REALLY THOUGHTFUL AND
DA GOT TO ASK HTAINING.
HE'S SAYING RIGHT THERE
TOMORROW.
TALK ABOUT SPINNING THE BALL OFF
THEIR FINGERS, HOW THEY RELEASE
JON: GARY SANCHEZ THINKS THAT
PITCH IS INSIDE AND LETS DAVID
RASKLY KNOW
INTERESTING WATCHING VERLANDER
IN THERE THAT ANIMATED.
THAT'S A ROPE INTO LEFT FIELD.
GARY SANCHEZ WITH HIS FIRST HIT
OF THE GAME AND THERE ARE TWO
ABOARD WITH TWO OUTS AND THE
INNING EXTENDS.
GLEYBER TOR HIT.
■■O■@0O■t@■@■O■C HE FRUSTRATINGS
NOT FEELING THE BALL OFF THE END
OF HIS FINGERS THE
BASEBALL, HOW HE FEELS HE'S
LETTING GO OF THE BASEBALL?
OR IS HE TALKING ABOUT WHERE HE
WANTS TO GET ON A CERTAIN PITCH.
HOW HE WANTS IT TO COME OFF THAT
BIRDIE FINGER, THE LAST FINGER
HE TOUCHES.
IS THAT THE BIRDIE FINGER?
JON: I THINK WE PROBABLY
SHOULDN'T GO DOWN THAT PATH.
DAVID: I DON'T WANT TO SAY
ANYTHING BAD ON TV.
JON: I KNOW YOU DON'T.
DAVID: WHAT I CALL IT.
JON: THAT'S LIKE YOU WERE
DRIVING THE CAR AND TOOK YOUR
HANDS OFF THE STEERING WHEEL AND
WERE LIKE, GO AHEAD, BOOG.
BY THE WAY, DAVID, ARE WE
DRIVING OFF THE CLIFF?
DAVID: I THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING
TO MAKE FUN OF ME FOR SURE.
JON: I WOULD HAVE BUT I WAS MORE
CONCERNED ABOUT THE F.C.C.■
HIT HARD TO THIRD.
BREGMAN AND THEY GO THE SHORT
WAY.
THAT IS THE THIRD OUT.
TIME TO STRETCH HERE IN HOUSTON
AND THE YANKEES WITH A TWO-RUN
ADVANTAGE.
Butterfinger?
Better Butterfinger.
[echoing]
Better Butterfinger...
♪
An improved recipe with
high quality jumbo peanuts
■ ■hh■■A■■■■■■■■■■■
that are crispety,
crunchety and peanut buttery.
♪
JON: FRIDAY, TOP RANK BOXING,
LOMACHENKO HEADLINING THE
STAPLES CENTER CARD EXCLUSIVELY
ON ESPN+, BOXING COMING YOUR WAY
AT 11:00 EASTERN AND UFC 236,
LIGHTWEIGHT CHAMPIONSHIP,
HOLLOWAY AND PORRIER.
SATURDAY, BOXING AND UFC.
MASAHIRO TANAKA, SIX INNINGS,
THREE HITS, EARNED RUN, TWO
WALKS, THREE STRIKEOUTS.
■■■■J■■■
DAVID: HE WAS PHENOMENAL.
TAKING OVER, ZACH BRITTON, JUST
A POWER SINKER.
COMPARE HIM WITH JONNY VENTERS
IN ATLANTA.
BOWLING BALL SINKER, YOU KNOW
IT'S COMING.
IT IS HARD TO SQUARE IT UP.
GOT TO GET HIM IN THE ZONE.
GET HIMZO■■ THAT SINKER
WILL FLATTEN OUT, IF YOU'RE THE
HOUSTON ASTROS.
JON: 0-1 TO CORREA NOW.
A YANKEE BULLPEN THAT SHOULD B
AS GOOD AS ANYONE'S PEN IN THE
GAME.
CERTAINLY THE ABILITY TO STRIKE
PEOPLE OUT WILL BE THERE ALL
SEASON LONG.
BRITTON IS A HARD THROWER.
MUCH DOESN'T INTO THE
STRIKEOUT CATEGORY.
IT'S STILL MORE GROUND BALL
ORIENTED.
THE OTHER WAY, BASE HIT.
QUICK CHECKIN, KEVIN CONNORS.
KEVIN: BRAVES-ROCKIES RIGHT NOW,
NICK MARKAKIS, OFF■ KYLE
FREELAND.
ATLANTA IS HITTING HIM TONIGHT.
TWO R.B.I. SINGLES.
BRAVES GRAB A 4-0 LEAD, TOP OF
THE THIRD INNING IN COLORADO.
JUST MOMENTS AGO, RHYS HOSKINS.
HE'D ALREADY GONE DEEP■á  ONCE,
MAKE IT TW
@2@2■■OF THE GAME, HIS
■ DD■f■ GAME WITH A HOME
RUN.
FOURTH CAREER MULTI-HOME RUN
GAME.
4-2 PHILLIES LEAD THE NATS.
YOU CAN SEE THAT ON ESPN+.
JON: PHILLIES GONNA SCORE SOME
RUNS THIS YEAR.
DAVID: MAP, THAT'S A DEEP
LINEUP.
REALMUTO, THAT PICKUP AND JOSINN
SEGURA, HE'S DONE NOTHING BUT
HIT HIS WHOLE CAREER.
THEY'VE GOT ANOTHER BIG-TIME
PLAYER.
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
JON: OUCH.ó■ó■ó■
DAVID: SO YOU WANT TO BE A
CATCHER, HUH?
JON: NO.
DAVID: OH, MAN.■/
JON: IT ALMOST LOOK LIKE IT GOT
HIM TWICE, ON THE BOUNCE.
DAVID: JUST NEED A LITTLE TIME,
CATCH HIS BREATH.
JON: GARY TAKING A MOMENT.
FANS, MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL IS
ALWAYS LIVE WITH MLB AT-BAT.
FOLLOW YOUR FAVORITE TEAM'S
ACTION WITH GAME TRACKING, VIDEO
HIGHLIGHTS, STATS, STANDINGS,
NEWS AND MORE.
DOWNLOAD MLB A■ TODAY.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN HIT IN THAT
SPOT AND HAD TO COME OUT OF THE
GAME?
DAVID: I DON'T THINK SO, NO.
IT USUALLY JUST TAKES A MINUTE.
THE ONES THAT HURT THE WORSE ARE
UNDERNEATH.
IF YOU GET THE BOUNCE AND
THAT'S THE ONE THAT REALLY
HURTS.
BUT YOU JUST NEED A MINUTE, GET
THOSE BUTTERFLIES OUT OF THE
STOMACH, FIGURE OUT WHAT TIME
ZONE YOU'RE IN.
JON: GURRIEL WITH THE COUNT AT
0-1.
MAN AT FIRST, 3-1, YANKEES.
DAVID: THEN YOU GET ONE IN THE
DIRT LIKE THA
DAVID: COME ON. THAT.
I'M JUST TRYING TO CATCH IT NOW.
NICE PIECE OF HITTING BY CORREA.
HAT TWO-SEAMER TO RIGHT
ON A LINE DRIVE SWING, EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO DO OFF A
GUY LIKE ZACH BRITTON.
JON: THEY GET ONE THERE.
CAN'T TURN IT.
NOT>>> Ió÷■ARD
ENOUGH.
DAVID: NICE PLAY B■1÷d URSHELA
BROKEN BAT.G IN, SOFTLY HITç
COMING IN, THROWING ACROSS HIS
BODY ON THE RUN.
GETS IT TO LEMAHIEU NICELY BUT
GURRIEL GETTING DOWN THE LINE
PRETTY WELL ON A SOFTLY HIT
GROUND BALL BUT NICE PLAY B
#>#>#í#í■■■ BASEMAN.
JON: ALEDMYS DIAZ WILL HIT IN
REDDICK'S■■;■@■>
FORMER CARDINAL, FORMER BLUE JAY
MASAHIRO TANAKA, SIX STRONG
OUT-DUELING JUSTIN VERLANDER.
THE YANKEES GETTING A HOMER FROM
AARON JUDGE AND R.B.I. SINGLES
FROM VOIT AND FRAZIER.
AND ALTUVE, SOLO HOMER FOR THE
ASTROS.
DID YOU HEAR JOHN STERLING'S
HOME RUN CALL FOR CLINT FRAZIER?
DAVID: DOWNTOWN GOES FRAZIER.
THAT WAS NICE.
JON: YOU CAN GIVE IT A SHOT.
DAVID: I STAY IN MY LANE.
JON: DIDN'T STOP ME FROM SAYING
NICE BLOCK EARLIER.
KNOCKED DOWN BY BRITTON.
HE'S GOING TO GO TO FIRST NOW.
THERE, TWO OUTS.
GURRIEL INTO SCORING POSITION.
DAVID: ALMOST HAD THIS ONE
THERE.
THAT TWO-SEAMER, GOT TO GET IT
UP IN THE ZONE.
DOES A NICE JOB KNOCKING IT
DOWN, GETTING THE OUT.
SMART PLAY THERE, DOESN'T PANIC.
MOVES HIS FEET, THROWS TO FIRST
FOR THAT SECOND OUT.
A LOT OF PITCHERS PANIC ON THAT
ONE.
JON: NOW WITH TWO DOWN AND A MAN
AT SECOND, IT IS TYLER WHITE.
THEIR D.H. THE LAST COUPLE OF
YEARS, WELL, A LOT OF THE TIME
WAS A GUY THAT THEY CALLED ELOSO
BONKO AND HE'S KIND OF BEEN
REPLACED BY ANOTHEROSO BLANCO.
DAVID: EVAN GATTIS.
THEY LOOK LIKE BROTHERS, DON'T
THEY?
JON: LIKE THE RUSSIAN NESTING
DOLL.
TYLER WHITE IS THE NEXT SMALLER
VERSION.
DAVID: PAUL BUNYON AND PAUL
BUNYON'S KID.
MY GOODNESS.
RUSSIAN NESTING DOLL.
THAT WAS GREAT.
NO, NO, WE HAVE ANOTHER D.H.
JUST A LITTLE BIT SMALLER AND HE
HITS ON THE RIGHT SIDE.
JON: BOTH THOSE GUYS CAN HIT.
WHITE WITH A GOOD EYE.
IT'S 3-0.
POINTING OUT THAT THIS VERSION
DOES WEAR BATTING GLOVES.
T■ REALO2■■■ O■hf#■1■■ ■ ■D■■ ■G
GLOVES.
NOW THE TYING RUN IS ON BASE.
JON SCIAMBI, DAVID ROSS, MINUTE
MAID PARK.
THE ROOF IS OPEN.
YOU AGAIN TOMORROW NIGHT AN HOUR
LATER, 8:00 EASTERN.
YOU CAN WAIT ON HAVING YOUR
CRACKER JACKS.
DAVID: KID JUST CAME BY AND GAVE
ME SOME CRACKER JACKS.
I REALLY WANT TO RIP INTO THESE
THINGS.
JON: TWO ON, TWO OUTS.
GURRIEL AT SECOND, WHITE AT
FIRST.
YANKEES UP 3-1.
IT WAS BRITTON WHO LAST
OFFSEASON RUPTURED HIS ACHILLES,
GOT THE LATE START AND THEN
EVENTUALLY WAS TRADED TO THE
YANKEES AND THEN THE YANKEES
JUST RE-SIGNED HIM AS A FREE
AGENT.
THEY ALSO SIGNED THE GUY THAT'S
UP IN THE BULLPEN, ADAM OTTAVINO
■ IS HAMMERED OUT TOWARDS
RIGHT CENTER FIELD, WELL STRUCK
AND THAT ONE IS OFF THE WALL.
GURRIEL IN, WHITE ON HIS HEELS.ç
AND SAFE!
A?í ROCKET BY THE CATCHER,
ROBINSON CHIRINOS AND WE'RE TIED
UP.
DAVID: THIS IS A GREAT PA■■■■d
■FgFABOUT■F■FgF■F■■gF■Fa■Fa
/Fk)■)■a■F■a■@
■a■@■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■d■ )d)d) )L
GET DEEP, TAKING THIS TWO-SEAMER
TO THE RIGHT SIDE.
YOU CAN SEE HEAD DOWN,C)C)■Wx x.
CRUSHES THIS BALL TO RIGHT
CENTER.
NICE CAROM.
BRETT GARDNER CATCHES THIS BALL
GREAT BUT HEADS-UP BASE RUNNING
BY TYLER WHITE GETTING ON HIS
HORSE FROM THE GIT-GO.
TYLER WHITE IS STRETCHING TO SEE
IF THAT BALL IS OFF THE BASE AND
WE'RE GOING■■■■■■■
THE PLATE, GIVING IT ALL HE'S
GOT.
GARY SANCHEZ, JUST SLIDES HIS
HAND UP.
GARY SANCHEZ WANTS THEM TO CHECK
IT OUT BUTOKS LIKE HE'S
SAFE.
JON: THEY'RE NOT GOING TO LOOK
AT IT, ARE THEY?
DAVID: LET'S CHECK OUT THIS PLAY
AT THE PLATE HERE.
BRETT GARDNER, GREAT JOB WITH
THE CAROM AND RELAY RACE, NICE
STRONG THROW BUT TYLER WHITE WAS
GETTING IT FROM THE GIT-GO.
JUST SLIDING THAT HAND IN THERE,
I THINK, BOOG.
JON: I'D SAY SAFE.
THAT WAS THE CALL■■7ñ■■ DAVID
RACKLEY.
♪ ♪
(chime)
Open an E*TRADE Premium Savings
Account
and earn 2.1% APY on your money.
That's over 20 times the
national average!
♪ ♪
What makes DiGiorno Crispy Pan
Pizza different than delivery?
♪ PAN PAN PAN PAAAAN ♪■
PN ♪
You bake it fresh
in its own pan!
Giving our DiGiorno pizza
a crispy, caramelized crust.Ñ■
♪ PAAAAN ♪
It's not Delivery,
It's DiGiorno.
Some say we're a little
spoiled in California.
But it isn't OUR fault.
Nope.
We didn't make all of this.
We're in awe, too.
Woo!
Yeah! Woo! Woohoo!
We get a lit-struck.
Did you see who's here?
What?
Sometimes we have to pinch
ourselves.
To make sure it's real.
Smoothie?
Ooo!
This is real.
I think it's a wig.
Stillisit!k we're spoiled?
It might take your breath
aw
t your
visitcalifornia.com
Huge mistake.
Kevin Harvick?
Choose Mobil 1
Synthetic instead.
It protects engines better
than conventional motor oil.
Yea you would say that,
you're wearing the logo.
How about now?
Get 250,000 miles
of protection.
Upgrade to Mobil 1.
I'm Paige, and well the little
thing that I like about the
Grilled Chicken Sandwich is
that it's pirfect.
It's juicy and it just has
all the right combinations.
I think I could be considered
a Grilled Chicken Sandwich
influencer.
My name is Frank and the
little thing I like
I love how juicy the chicken is
but there's also the tomatoes■
and the lettuce and
it's incredible.
Make sure you get it
with waffle fries,
because that's my favorite.
JON: BACK IN HOUSTON.
JON SCIAMBI, DAVID ROSS.
ADAM OTTAVINO -- BRIAN CASHMAN
MAKING SURE THAT BULLPEN WOULD
BE SOLID AND THIS GUY WITH
NASTY, NASTY BREAKING■h■■RR■;■;X
AND A BIG SWING AND A MISS■>■>óM
SPRINGER.
Ñ7Ñ7■>Ñ>Ñ>■>Ñ>■í■í THE TOUGHEST
PITCHES TO HIT IN ALL OF
BASEBALL LAST YEAR WAS THIS
GUY'S SLIDER DOWN AND AWAY TO
RIGHT-HANDED HITTERS.
ANOTHER FORMER CLOSER.
SEEMS LIKE THE YANKEES DO THAT
EVERY YEAR, FIND CLOSERS FROM
OTHER TEAMS AND STACK THAT
BULLPEN.
GUYS LIKE BRITTON, OTTAVINO.
JON: SEE OTTAVINO WEARING THAT
ZERO ON HIS BACK.
HE IS THE FIRST PLAYER IN THE
HISTORY OF THE YANKEES TO WEAR
ZERO.
IT LOOKS WEIRD.
DAVID: IT DOES■ LOOK WEIRD.
BACKUP SLIDER HERE, GEORGE
SPRINGER WAITING OHING
TO■4
■=■88L■x■■Uy■S SWING, HE'S
CONFUSED.
DIDN'T COME BACK THE WAY HE
WANTED.
JON: HE GREW UP IN NEW YORK, IN
BROOKLYN.
WENT TO COLLEGE AT NORTHEASTERN
AND BOSTON.ñOñ■oh
ç■wCwC■ g oooo■)■y■a■■ ■ :w oFAR
AND THAT IS THAT.
CHIRINOS TIES IT UP WITH A
DOUBLE.
OTTAVINO GETS OUT OF A JAM.
at y.
,
hidden in the depths
of this soft taco,
you'd find Crunchy...
Melty...
Nachos.
For just one dollar.
Would you believe me?
Or are you just seeing things?
The new $1 Loaded Nacho Taco
from Taco Bevings
Value Menu.■■qálue B.
ò The new $1 Loaded Nacho Taco
[outdoor ambiance]
♪
Hi, Mrs. Gorman.
Hey, Theo.
police radio: I have
the stolen vehicle in sight.
[police siren]
♪
■7<7<7         ♪
[police siren]
police radio:
it's safe to slow it down.
♪
OnStar Advisor:
Mr. Grantham, this is OnStar.
The police have your vehicle.
JARDIANCE asks...
When it comes to
type 2 diabetes,
are you thinking about
your heart?
Well, I'm managing my A1C,
so I should be all set.
Actually, you're still at risk
for a fatal heart attack
or stroke.
That's where JARDIANCE comes in.
It reduces the risk of dying
from a cardiovascular event
for adults who have type 2
diabetes and known heart diseas.
That's why the American Diabetes
Association recommends
the active ingredient
in JARDIANCE.
And it lowers A1C?
With diet and exercise.
JARDIANCE can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration,
genital yeast or
urinary tract infections,
Ketoacidosis is a serious
side effect
that may be fatal.
A rare, but life-threatening,
bacterial infection
in the skin of the perineum
could occur.
Stop taking JARDIANCE
and call your
doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of this bacterial infection,
ketoacidosis,
or an allergic reaction.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe
kidney problems.
Taking JARDIANCE
with alurea
or insulin may cause
low blood sugar.
So, what do you think?
Now I feel I can do more
to go beyond lowering A1C.
Ask your doctor about
JARDIANCE today.
JON:ESPN'S TELECAST OF MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL IS PRESENTED BY
USAA, INSURANCE, BANKING AND
INVESTMENTS TAILORED FOR THE
MILITARY COMMUNITY.
BACK AT MINUTE MAID PARK AND
RUMOR HAS IT THAT IF YOU HAVE A
CLEVER COMMENT, MLB WILL REPLY.
FOLLOW MLB ON FACEBOOK,
INSTAGRAM AND TWITTER.
HERE'S RYAN KRESSLEY.
DAVID: HE'S A GUY, SLIDER,
CURVEBALL, MONSTER.
THROW IT OVER HALF THE TIME.
GREAT COMMAND.
HE CAN RUN IT UP THERE 95, 97
MILES AN HOUR.
GOT TO RESPECT THE HEATER.
JON: ASTROS WITH A COUPLE OF
CHANGES.
DAVID: JAKE MARISNICK IN CENTER.
SPRINGER OVER TO RIGHT.
JON: MARISNICK IS ARGUABLY THEIR
BEST OUTFIELD DEFENDER.
DAVID: TOOK THE WORDS OUT OF MY
MOUTH.
I LIKE IT WHEN HE'S ROAMING
CENTER.
JON: AND HE'S BIG BUT HE CAN GO
GET IT.
IT'S AN INTERESTING ONE TO ME,
AS WELL, IN THAT WHEN YOU ASK
GEORGE SPRINGER WHAT HE PREFERS,
HE LIKES PLAYING RIGHT BETTER
THAN CENTER AND MORE OFTEN THAN
NOT I FEEL LIKE THE GUYS WILL
TELL YOU, I LIKE PLAYING CENTER
BETTER.
EAH, YOU RARELY HEAR
THAT.
YOU GET TO SEE EVERYTHING FROM
CENTER FIELD.
YOU GET MORE CENTER FIELDERS
COMING IN AND COMPLAINING ABOUT
THE PITCH■■■ CALLING.
THEY'REBAD DAY AND
THEY THINK THEY'REIRES IN
DEXTER FOWLER USED TO RUN IN,
WHERE'S THAT PITCH?
THAT WAS THREE STRIKES HE MISSED
THAT INNING!
JON: BIRD CHASES, SWING AND A
MISS.
CHECK IN WITH KEVIN IN THE
STUDIO.
RHYS HOSKINS, A COUPLE OF
HOMERS, GIVES THE PHILS A■h
LEAD.
NINTH INNING, RYAN DOZIER, HOW
ABOUT HIS FIRST WITH THE
NATIONALS.
CAME OVER IN JANUARY.
TYING RUN, 90 FEET AWAY WITH
KURT SUZUKI, FLIES OUT TO RIGHT.
PATTY IN SHACK LOC DOWN HIS
FIRST■■çk■[■?/wwwo■■ NESHEK LOCS
FIRS■ SAVE.
N PRESSLY, YOU TALK
ABOUT A STEAL OF AN OPPOSITION.
THEY -- ACQUISITION.
THEY GOT HIM JULY LAST YEAR FROM
THE■@■T DID AN
HE IS A STRIKEOUT■■& MACHINE
THATóv/W SWEEPY BREAKING BALLq;â
TH■á
::■ GOT TWO OF THEM BUT
YOU TALK ABOUT A BREAKING BALL
THAT WORKS BOTH PLANES GOING THE
HORIZONNITAL AND VERSATILE.
DAVID: HE CAN GET OUT RIGHTIES
AND LEFTIES WITH TWO DIFFERENT
PLANES BREAKING BALLS.
JON: LAST YEAR WITH THE ASTROS,
26 APPEARANCES, 23 1/3 INNINGS,
GAVE UP TWO EARNED RUNS.
32s4ñ;ñ;■;ñ;ñ;■;■;■;■;■;■;■;■;qF
THEY WERE FIRST IN THEIR LEAGUE
IN OVERALL E.R.A. AND STARTERS
E.R.A. AND BULLPEN E.R.A.
ALLOWED THE FEWEST RUNS IN THE
MAJORS.
YOU ALLOW THE FEWEST RUNS IN THE
MAJORS PLAYINHE GAMES IN
THIS PARK AND PLAYING IN THE
AMERICAN LEAGUE WITH THE D.H.,
THEIR RUN PREVENTION LAST YEAR
WAS REALLY GOOD.
THEYAY A LOT OF ATTENTION TO
THEIR DEFENSE.
A.J. HINHEM OUT THERE.
THEY DO THEIR DEFENSIVE
MAINTENANCE WORK, AS HE CALLS
IT, WHERE THEY TAKE A MODIFIED
INFIELD, TAKE TWO OUT OF EVERY
THREE GAMES, ANECDOTALLY, I
DON'T BELIEVE THERE'S ANOTHER
TEAM THAT DOES THAT AS MUCH AS
THEY DO.
DAVID: I JUST LOVE HIS COMMENT
IN THAT CONVERSATION, I'M JUST
OBSESSED WITH DEFENSE.
THAT'S WHY YOU WIN, BECAUSE
YOU'RE PREVENTING RUNS.
FOR ME, THAT'S SO IMPORTANT.
ESPECIALLY WITH THE PITCHING
STAFF AND THE LINEUP YOU HAVE.
THAT'S A GOOD SWING.
HE'S ALL OVER THIS BREAKING BALL
RIGHT HERE.
JUST MISSES■q■■úúú
PRETTY GOOD PASS AT THAT NASTY
BREAKING BALL AS WE WERE TALKING
ABOUT EARLIER.
JON: TO CENTER.
MARISNICK IS THERE.
JOSE ALTUVE WILL LEAD IT OFF.■g.
Do you need the most
trusted battery
in your noise cancelling
headphones?
Maybe not.
Maybe you could trust you won't
be next to a loud eater.
(eating potato chips loudly)
Or you could just trust
Duracell. (silence)
♪♪
Mom! He's Blinking too loud.
Sorry, is that too loud?
You don't need any more hormones
in your house.
That's why you chose Kraft
Natural Cheese.
Made with fresh milk without the
added hormone rbST.
It's Cheese as it should be.
GATORADE ZERO.
ALL THE ELECTROLYTES.
ZERO SUGAR.
♪♪
♪♪ GET MORE OUT ■
New lower price.
Wow. That's a lot
of asparagus.
Yeah, you said get
a bunch of asparagus.
Oh, you...
bunch.
I... thought you kinda...
>> THIS COPYRIGHTED TELECAST IS
PRESENTED BY THE ■■■■■■■
JON: JOSE ALTUVE, SELL ANDén■■■■
ALL-STAR, THREE TIMES HE'S WON A
BATTING TITLE, HE'S DEVELOPED
SOME POWER.
SOLO HOMER EARLIER TONIGHT■f
ñññ■ñ■p■■ ñ■!L■■■■■■■■== SCIAMB.
B@B@ ANDYOU PREFER.
DAVID: I PREFER THAT.
JON: 0-21'S NOT THAT BAD.
YOU'RE STILL HOT.
DAVID: BROCK HOLT.
THANKS, BUDDY.
APPRECIATE THE LISTEN AND THE
LOVE.
GOD KNOWS I GET NONE AROUND
HERE.
JON: ALTUVE, THEN BREGMAN, THEN
BRANTLEY AGAINST ONE OF THE
YANKEES TOP RELIEVERS.
REMEMBER, BETANCES IS ON THE
D.L. FOR THE YANKEES.
SEVERINO, THEIR ACE STARTER, IS
ON THE SHELF.
THEY SHOULD GET SABATHIA BACK
SOME TIME THIS WEEKEND AND AARON
BOONE WAITING ON TLIKES OF
STANTON, ANDUJAR P.THE ANDUJAR
INJURY, REALLY QUICKLY, IS
INTERESTING, IN TERMS OF IT'S A
LABRUM ISSUE IN HIS RIGHT
SHOULDER AND HE MIGHT BE BACK IN
A COUPLE OF WEEKS OR MIGHT NEED
TO HAVE SURGERY AND BE DONE FOR
THE YEAR.
DAVID: SHOULDER IS A TRICKY
INJURY.
YOU ALWAYS WORRY ABOUT THOSE --
HOW SERIOUS IS IT.
JON: FLIPS THE CORNER.
NASTY PITCH FROM THE
RIGHT-HANDER.
DAVID: THAT'S SO TOUGH WITH THAT
SLIDER HE SWUNG AND MISSED AT
EARLIER.
WATCH HE STARTS THIS BACKDOOR
TWO-SEAMER 93 OFF THE EDGE AND
BRINGS IT BACK TO CLIP THE
K-ZONE.
NASTY PITCH.■=■=■=■=>=?=■=?=?=■■
WHEN YOU'RE DOING THAT, X'ING
THAT OUTSIDE CORNER JUST THE TOP
BOOG: F THE CHEESE, AS YOU SAY,
JON: RIGHT THERE AND ALTUVE KNEW
IT.
DAVID: WHAT MAKES HIM SO TOUGH.
HE'S GOT THAT CROSS-BODY FIRE
AND HE'S WORKING AWAY.
YOU SEE THAT BALL STARTING DOWN
THE MIDDLE.
JOUVN'T KNOW WHAT
DO.P=■=
FREEZES IN HERE.
SLIDER, MIDDLE-MIDDLE.
THAT'S WHAT HE SETS UP WITH THE
THROWING.OZE HIM THERE FOR A REY
GOOD HITTER WHO LIKES TO SWING.
JON: THIS GUY, ADAM OTTAVINO,
ANOTHER ONE OF THOSE DISCIPLES
OF DRIVE LINE IN SEATTLE, A
PLACE WE GET TO VISIT.
AND PITCH DESIGN.
HE HAS HIS OWN CAMERA, THE RAP■E
THROWS>?7?7?7?7■;■;■#■/■/■/■■■■E
OFFSEASON AND THAT'S HOW HE
HELPED DO IT BUT WITH THE HELP
OF THE FOLKS FROM DRIVE LINE.
DAVID: AMAZING.
HOW GUYS ARE TAKING THAT AND
BUYING THEIR OWN MACHINES AND
MAKING THEIR OW BULLPENS,
COLLECTING ALL THE DATA THEY CAN
TO■n IMPIR
AND■1IT'S■Y
YOU SEE GUYS LIKE TREVOR BAUER,
ONE OF THEIR MARQUEE PLAYERS
THEY TALK ABOUT.
THIS GUY'S PRETTY DARN GOOD
HERE.
JON: THE PITCH DESIGN THING I
THINK IS INTERESTING IN TERMS OF
WATCHING IN SUPER SLOW MO, THE
BALL COME OUT OF THE HAND AND
THEN LOOKING AT THE DATA AND THD
TEAMS HAVE IT MORE AND MORE
WHERE THEY SIT THERE AND THE
PI■■K AND LOOK AT,
WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE COMING
OUT OF THE HAND AND WHAT WAS THE
DATA TO MATCH IT.
DAVID: WE JUST SAW TWO GREAT
PITCHERS IN THE DUGOUT FOR
HOUSTON TALKING ABOUT THEIR
FINGERS AND WHERE THE FINGERS
ARE ON THE BASEBALL.
THAT'S WHAT THESE CAMERAS ARE
ABLE TO DO, AND SLOW DOWN, HELP
THEM ANALYZE WHAT THEY'RE
FEELING AND WHAT IS ACTUALLY
HAPPENING SO THEY CAN MAKE THE
MINOR ADJUSTMENTS AND GIVE THEM
THE MOST PRODUCTIVE SPIN ON
THEIR PITCHES.
JON: THEY MATCH THE VISUAL DATA
WITH THE FIELD.
THAT'S THE PERFECT THING.
BECAUSE IN THE PAST, YOU'D GET
THE FEEL OF, OK, DAVID, WAS THAT
A GOOD SLIDER?
YEAH, I THINK THAT WAS A GOOD
SLIDER, IT FELT LIKE A GOOD
SLIDER.
NOW THEY GO BACK AND LOOK AT HOW
IT COMES OUT THE OF THE HAND AND
THEN YOU LOOK AT THE DATA AND
THE SPIN RATE IS WHAT THEY WANT.
OK.
■HAT'S WHAT A GOOD ONE SHOULD■
DAV■ THE BREAK.
ALL THAT INFORMATION IS
IMPORTANT.
MO- THESE TEAMS ARE÷■ñí■■ LABS S
IN TO GET THAT FEEDBACK.
JON: BACK TO THE STUDIO AND
KEVIN CONNORS.
KEVIN: BACK AND FORTH THEY DID,
DODGERS-CARDINALS.
3-2 GAME, BOT THE SIXTH,
TWO ON, R.B.I. SINGLE OFF THE
BAT OF JOSÉ MARTÍNEZ.
COMES OFF JOE KELLY BUT THE
INNING WAS NOT OVER.
KELLY, WILD PITCH, PAUL
GOLDSCHMIDT SCORES THE GO-AHEAD
RUN.
KELLY'S E.R.A. 13.50.
CARDS LEAD TOP SEVEN.■77■w
DAVID: THAT'S SOMEONE THEY MEDE.
SPENT A LOT OF MONEY ON HIM THIS
OFFSEASON AND THE WAY HE ENDED
THE SEASON WITH THE RED SOX, IT
WAS REALLY STRONG.
THEY'RE WAITING FOR HIM TO FIND
HIS GROOVE.
THEY NEED HIM SETTING JANSEN.
JON: GO-AHEAD RUN IS AT FIRST.
ALEX BREGMAN DELIVERING A GOOD
AT-BAT.
RE'S■ ■ ■ ■ BRANTLEY.
IS IS SUBTLE BUT, AGAIN,
BASEBALL 2019, YOU SEE THE
SHIFTING SO YOU'VE GOT TORRES,
LEMAHIEU AND BIRD.
BUT THE OTHER THING THAT FACTORS
IN, THE STRIKEOUT.
THIS IS WHY THEY SIGNED MICHAEL
BRANTLEY, BECAUSE THEY NEED
SOMEONE TO PUT THE BALL IN PLAY.
DAVID:I LIKE HOW YOU USE, AH,
BUT WAIT.
BREGMAN ñ/ñ/OND.■@T■>■>■>Z>Z>■>.
THE STRIKEOUT IS SUCH A BIG
FACTOR IN THIS SPORT AND THEY GO
AND SIGN A GUY THAT IS SO GOOD
AT MAKING CONTACT.
THIS IS A GUY THAT GIVES
YOU THAT PROFESSIONAL AT-BAT AND
HITS FROM THE 8  SIDE IN
BETWEEN THOSE GREAT HITTERS.
JUST STAYS ON THIS SLIDER,
STAYING UP THE MIDDLE, A TRUE
PRO AT-BAT, AS YOU SAID, HE'S■■
GOT BASE RUNNING BY BREGMAN
KNOWING THAT SHIFT IS THERE AND
THAT'S AN EASY FIRST TO THIRD
FOR HIM AND THE HOUSTON ASTROS
HAVE SOMETHING WORKING.
JON: ONE OUT, RUNNERS AT THE
CORNERS.
CARLOS CORREA.
THAT LOW STRIKEOUT RATE ANDfn■P■
■@■sN 2v■,■ FASTBALL FOR
A STRIKE.
WE'VEOME ROCKETS TONIGHT,
BY THE WAY.?LASI BAL■1■1■1■■p■pN
HOUR.
THE TWO TEAMS COMBINED, THERE
HAVE BEEN 10 BALLS HIT 100 MILES
AN HOUR OR HARDER TONIGHT.
BREGMAN AT THIRD, THE GO-AHEAD
RUN.
BRANTLEY AT FIRST.
BROKEN BAT ROLLER UP ALONG
FIRST.
IT'S GOING77GET THE RUN IN AND
EVERYBODY'S SAFE!
THAT'S ABOUT AS WEIRD A SPIN COS
THE OUT.
DAVID: I'D LIKE TO SEE THE EXIT
VELO OFF THIS ONE.
WE TALKED ABOUT THE 10 HARD-HIT
BALLS.
THIS ONE PUSHES AHEAD THE
THEY SAY GOOD HITTERS GET■dii■b
JAMMED
■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■  S
BALL, TWO-SEAM FASTBALL.
WHEN YOU START THIS NASTY
SLIDER, YOU'RE TRYING TO PROTECT
AGAINST.
THIS IS SMART HITTING.EXIT VELOR
WITH A 2% LAUNCH ANGLE.■■
JON: WAY TO GO!
DAVID: WHAT WAS IMPRESSIVE, TOO,
BREGMAN OFF THE SWING OF THE
BAT, NO HESITATION, SCORE
EASY AND PHENOMENAL JOB BY BIRD
NOT PANICKING.