CLIFF AND STEVE KEIM.
THIS IS A TEAM RIGHT NOW THAT
ULTIMATELY HAS TO DECIDE BIG
TIME ON KYLER MURRAY■8 OROSH
ROSE.%%%■■■E THE MOST UNDERTHE D
ZACH TAILOR AND THELSa■D!aDaD■a
HEAD COACHES.
WHAT IS TOhHE CULTURE.OW US WHA.
SEE YOU
>>> TODAY'S OPENING TIP, THE
DUNK AROUND NBA TWITTER LAST
NIGHT.
CARUSO MAY NOT BE THE HERO
LAKERS FANS WANT, GUYS.
BUT HE MAY BE THE HERO THEY
NEED.
>> OTHER THAN GETTING UP OUT OF
THEIR SEATS DURINGTIME-OUTS.
THAT'S A MAJOR■7I■÷■1■7 FREE AGT
SIGNIN OTHER THANTIME-OUTS■>■>
THE BREAK.
>> THAT WAS AWESOME.
>> THAT GAME WAS SO BAD.
Y'ALL WANT TO HAVE THAT GAME ON
AST NIGHT, BUT YOU DON'T ANT TO
GAME?
>> THAT'S NOT OUR NETWORK.
KIDDING.
I GUES GO WITH WHAT THEY
THINK WILL BEHIGHER-RATED, ECAU
HI HOME ■ME.
IT'S OUR TWORK THAT IS N■2■2■2■I
NICHOLS, WITHM■[■[■[■[■[■[■[R■[.
■IIS,GUYS,■I■IA■IA&A&A&■I■I■I■II
WE HAVE A FUN STUDIO AUDIENCE
TODAY.
SHOUT OUT TO THEM.
COMING UP, WE'LL DEBUT MY
CONVERSATION WITH DWYANE WADE.
GABRIELLE .■ ■UNION-ó THEIR
BEAUTIFUL BABY■  AS
AND WE HEAD TO ■PHILLY, WHERE TE
GREEK FREAK HAD 35 POINTS, IN A
HUGE WIN OVER THE SIXERS.
4 OF HIS 5 BLOCKS ON JOEL
EMBIID.
A LOT OF MVP VOTERS GOING INTO
>>■ I DON'T KNOW WHY.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK THIS
PERFORMANCE DID FOR THE MVP
VOTERS?
>> FOR ME,T DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING.
FOR ME, I WAS ALREADY VOTING FOR
HIM.
FOR OTHERS, IT SOLIDIFIED.
BUT I HATE TALKING ABOUT THIS,
BECAUSE JAMES HARDEN HAD SUCH A
PHENOM SEASON.
HE COULD VERY WELL BE MVP THIS
YEAR.
■■AUYOU TAKE
GIANOFF TM, WHERE
WOULD THEY BE?
WITHOUT JAMESñ■ ■ñEN,HEY STILL
■n■n■n■n■n■n#n■n#n#n#n#n#n NUMBE
D THROUGHOUT PLAYOFFS,
CLINCHED THE NUMBER ONE.
IT'S HUGE.
>> AND JAMES HARDEN, HOLDING UP
HIS TEAM WITH CAPELA AND PAUL
OUT.
BUT A LOT OF BUCKS ARE OUT, T>>T
THIS GAME LAST NIGHT.
WATCHING EMBIID AND GIANNIS
BATTLE.
AND GIANNIS, IT'S A TIGHT GAME,
HE WINKS AT HIS TEAMMATES, LIKE,
I GOT THIS.
THIS IS WHAT I WANT TO SEE.
BACK IN 07, LeB 29 OUT
OF 30 POINTS IN DETROIT.
THAT WAS WHEN HE ARRIVED, AND
UNDERSTOOD HE COULD DOMINATE A
GAME.
WE'RE ON THE EDGE WITH GIAN
I THINK WE MAY SEE IT THIS
POSTSEASON, IF HE TAKES THE
SERIES, ESPECIALLY A ROAD GAME.
THEY'RE BEHIND THE WHOLE GAME.
IN PHILLY, I KNOW JIMMY BUTLER
DIDN'T PLAY.
BUT THAT EXCITED ME ABOUT WHEN
LeBRON WON IN 2007, 9 OF
NEXT 11 YEARS, LeBRON WON.
NOW, THIS COULD BE GIANNIS
TAKING THE TORCH.
I'M SO EXCITED.
>> AND I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S
SOCIAL MEDIA OR RADIO, BUT IT
DIDN'T USED TO FEEL TO ME, IF
SAID YOU LIKED THISGUY,THE
OTHER GUY IS AUTOMATICALLY
TRASH.
BUT NOW, IF YOU LIKETHIS GUY, I
CAN'T BELIEVE YOU HATE JAMES
HARDEN.■O■O■O■I
ALL THE TI■■O■OA■■I■A■■Ñ
ALSOIS GUY IS GOOD.
THERE'S THAT.
JOEL EMBIID WAS LISTED AS
QUESTIONABLE HEADING INTO LAST
FALL ON HIS BACK AFTER ONE
THE GIANNISBLOCKS.
PLAYED A TEAM HIGH
MINUTES, POSTED HIS ABSURD
LINE, POINTS, 13■ UNDS, 13
ASSISTS.
BUT SHOULD HE HAVE EVEN PLAYED
LAST NIGHT?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY,
AUS THEY KEEP
SHUT HIS EE,■# INDICATES IT'S R
BOTHERING HIM.
HE'S BORDERLINE HERE, GOING IN
AND OUT OF THE GAME.
BUT LOOKS REALLY GOOD WHEN HE
PLAYS.
HE WAS AWESOME IN THIS GAME.
AND I WAS JUST AS EXCITED ABOUT
EMBIID GOING BACK DOWN AND
SCORING ON HIM OVER AND OVER
AGAIN.
!eAIN.
>> HE'S WITH■@@@
HE'S A TRUE "7"7"■■00!■3■"■■■3■
KNOW OUR BODIES.
FOR HIM, I THINK IT'S GOOD THAT
HE CAME BACK, BECAUSE YOU DON'T
WANT TO COME BACK WHEN IT'S
PLAYOFF TIME, AND YOU DON'T
HAVE, YOU KNOW, THE WIND THAT
YOU NEED, THE RHYTHM THAT■■■]■/Q
UNDER HIS BELT BEFORE THE
PLAYOFFS START.
AND WITH ALL THE GAMES HE
MISSED, IT DIDN'T LOOK LIKE HE
MISSED A BEAT.
■áLAD HE PLAYED.ED WITH ALL THE
>> YOU GOT TO SEE A TOP FIVE
PLAYER OFFENSIVELY DEFENSIVELY,
GO AGAINST AOP FIVE
>> AND GIANNIS HAD A LITTLE BIT
MORE AMMO, BECAUSE PEOPLE WERE
SAYING THE LAST TIME THEY
PLAYED, T
MBID A■L,
DEFEND■R■R■R■yPUT THAT TO@■@■■
WE GOT THIS, JOEL AND BLEDSOE
AND SCOTT, MAYBE THEY WERE
PLAYING DODGEBALL.
>> JOEL, YOU CAN'T THROW THE
BALL AT SOMEBODY AND NOT EXPECT
■■#■■■■7CE. >> IT ■H A LI}
>> DO YOU GUYS GIVE BLEDSOE A
PASS?
>> HE THREW IT AT HIM FIRST, IT
WAS ONLY RIGHT FOR HIM TO THROW
IT BACK.
>> COME ON.
>> OH, NO.
>> THAT'S NOT THE SAME, GUYS.p87
>> OH!■p
>> YOU GUYS ARE PROMOTING --
THAT WAS A GAME OF DODGEBALL
RIGHT THERE.
■C■C■C■C FACsL
■@■@ WE JUST ■I■yOW
■IYOUR■IHIGHLIGHTS ON  SHOND■■H÷
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT WATCHING,
KIDS.
>> AND I HOPE■■■@■@ x=:=<=■= PL
CAN'T GET ELIMINATED FROM THE
GAME.
ON THE PLAY, EMBIID GAVE GIANNIS
ABOUT TEN FEET, GIANNIS WAS
LIKE, I'LL GET A THREE.
GIANNIS HAD A MOMENT.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND WE SAW THIS WITH MORRIS AND
SMART, I'IX■I■Oód■d■d■g
■I■■■■■FOR
LAST■■■MONTH.
>> MARCUS S ■>>R ■%@%■%LI@%@%■%
REACT LIKE THIS.■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
WE JUST■■■■ P■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■H
E'RE GOING TO■■■■■sGS ■■■■
UUSE WE■■■■■■C2■■ HAVE AN UNUSU
FORMAT.
WHAT IS IT?
>> IT'S A MAKE OR MISS LEAGUE.
>> MAKE/MISS.
IT'S A MAKE OR MISS LEAGUE.
>>B8 YOU GO, KAWHI EONARD.■■
E, DE'AARON FOX SIZING UP CO
STEPBACK, TOO.
>> THAT WAS, LIKE, EVERYTHING.
>> HEH■■■■■ THE BLENDER
THERE.
>> COME HERE, YOUNG BULL.
>> THE CAVS ARE DOING A HEAVY
CAMPAIGN FOR HIM TO BE ON THE
ALL-ROOKIETEAM.
>> THEY WANT THE F■úTEAM, IT
HE'CK■ IT UP, BUT MAYBE NOT■
THE FIRST TEAM.
MISS, LANDING, COREY BREWER.G■!
>>COMES DOWN VERYAWKWARDLY,
GOT UPDER HIS POWER.
>> THE HEADBANDOTECTED HIM
>> HE DID NEED TO GET CHECKED
OUT, BUT THEN HE CHECKED BACK
>> I THINK HE'S AT THE POINT IN
HIS CAREER WHERE IT'S LAY-UP
TIME.
>> THAT PHOTO■1■1 JUST
PHENOMENAL.
IF I'M HIM, I'M HAVING■AT
FRAMED AAYING, I WALKED A WAY
FROM THAT.
>> WE'RE SO CRUEL ON THIS SHOW.
WHY DID YOU HAVE TOj■ PAUSE HIMN
IDAIR LIKE THAT?■■■■■ SOOD.■@■8
MAKE, VISION.
FIRST HE GETS THE L, THEN
STEPH THROWS THE RIDICULOUS
PASS.
EVEN FOR LAKERS FANS, THIS WA
LOOK AT THAT. OF THE GAME.
SKILLS.LS, PEOPLE.■d
AND HE LD.
>> I DID TALK TO STEPH ABOUT THE
CONTACT.
AMAZING MUCH CLEARER THE
COURT IS.■0
HE SAID, I CAN SEE THE PUTT MUCH
BETTER NOW, TOO.
THERE YOU GO.STIME TO RUN IT BA.
THE BEST BEHIND THE BACK DIMES
OF ALL TIME.
1999.  THRE■
>> WHAT IS BETTERHAN THAT?
>> THAT'S WHY WE HAVE BOMBER.
>> LET ME■2P)■h■E■FAb■u5y■=■■■E7
NUMBER TWO.
WHAT ABOUT THAT?
>> OKAY.
>> THAT'S BASICALLY WHAT STEPH
DID LAST NIGHT.
BUT IT WAS HARDER THAN WHAT
STEPH DID, BECAUSE KEVIN DURANT
WAS OPEN.
CHARLES BARKLEY, OF ALL PEOPLE.
WATCH THIS PASS.
>> WHOA!
>> DID YOU KNOW HE COULD MOVE
LIKE THAT?
>> I DIDN'T KNOW HE COULD PASS
LIKE HAT.
>> I THINK NUMBER TC DIFFICULTYE
■[■]■#■■■■■.
>> COMING FR■ HIM
REALLY GOOD .
>> THAT WAS SOME HIGH-LEVEL
SHADE.
SOMETHING OTHER THAN -- I WAS
VERY IMPRESSED.
SO MUCH MORE COMING YOUR WAY.
UP NEXT, MY CONVERSATION WITH
DWYANE WADE, WITH THE FINAL
GAMES OF HIS CAREER APPROACHING.
HERE'S A LITTLE SNEAK PEEK.
>> KOBE HAS SET THIS
UNBELIEVABLE, IMPOSSIBLE BAR
THAT PEOPLE FEEL THAT, IN YOUR
LAST GAME, YOU HAVE TO SCORE 60.
>> IF IT TURNS OUT YOU GO INTO
THE GAME KNOWING FOR SURE YOU
GUYS ARE OUT OF IT, ARE WE GOING
FOR 40?
>> WELL, I'M GOING TO SHOOT.
So I can buy from
Enterprise Car Sales and you'll
take ANY trade-in?
's right!
Great!
Here you go...
Well, it does need
to be a vehicle.
But - I need this out of
my house.
(VO) With fair, transparent
value for every trade-in...
Enterprise makes it easy.
Don't do it.
Anthony Davis?
Choose Mobil 1
Synthetic instead.
It protects engines better
than conventional motor oil.
Uh, my oil works
just fine thank you.
Can it keep your engine
in excellent condition
for over 250,000 miles?
You know, you look
much taller on TV.
The camera adds six feet.
Seems like a thing people
would know. But I didn't.
Get 250,000 miles
of protection.
Upgrade to Mobil 1.
>>> SO, IT'S BEEN 16 YEARS THAT
YOU'VE SEEN DWYANE WADE, HAS WON
NBA TITLES, HE'S A 13-TIME
ALL-STAR.
BUT HERE'S WHAT YOU HAVEN'T
SEEN.
I WAS ABLE TO GO DOWN TO MIAMI
THIS WEEKEND, AND GO INSIDE OF
HIS HOME WITH HIS LOVELY WIFE
AND BEAUTIFUL NEW BABY, AND TAKE
STOCK OF WHERE HE'S BEEN THIS
YEAR, AND WHAT HE'S LOOKING
FORWARD TO AS HE GOES INTO
RETIREMENT.
IT'S BEEN A YEAR, AND ONE HE
DIDN'T EXPECT.
TAKE A LISTEN.
SO, THANK YOU FOR WELCOMING US
INTO YOUR HOME.
I THOUGHT THIS WAS VERY
APPROPRIATE, WHAT'S BEHIND YOU.
I SWEAR, THE LAST COUPLE OF
MONTHS, YOU WERE SOME OF THE
MOST CALM AND ZEN I'VE SEEN YOU
IN YOUR CAREER.
WHERE ARE YOU MENTALLY?
>> I'M COOL.
I'M JUST CHILLING, JUST
ENJOYING, LIKE, THE PROCESS.
I'M ENJOYING THE PROCESS, LIKE,
DAILY.
IT IS A LOT OF LAST TIMES.
EVERY DAY, THE LAST TIME YOU'LL
DO THIS.
>> THE LAST MEATBALL I'LL EAT IN
THE MIAMI HEAT CAFETERIA.
AND NONE OF THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO
HAPPEN, YOU TOLD ME, I THINK,
THREE TIMES LAST SUMMER, I'M
DONE.
I'M NOT COMING BACK FOR THIS
LAST YEAR.
I'M DONE.
YOU TOLD YOUR FAMIU WERE
DONE?
>> YEAH.
I REMEMBER TALKING, AND I WAS
LIKE, MAN, I DON'T KNOW IF I
WANT TO DO THIS ANYMORE.
THEY WERE LIKE, WHAT?
I DON'T EVEN LIKE COMING TO
SHOOTAROUND IN THE MORNING.
THERE WERE THINGS I STARTED NOT
TO LIKE.
>> YOU TALKED TO CARMELO
ANTHONY, IT WAS A CONSEQUENTIAL
DECISION.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
>> HE SAID, LET'S GET DOWN TO
IT.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
RETIRING?
I SAW IT IN HIS VOICE AND HIS
EYES, HE WAS LIKE, YO, YOU CAN'T
RETIRE AND NOT ALLOW US TO
CELEBRATE YOU OR TO CELEBRATE
THE CAREER YOU'VE HAD.
TO ME, IT WAS AN EYE-OPENER.
AND C.P. CALLED ME, AND SAID THE
SAME THING.
SO I SAID, LET ME THINK ABOUT
THIS DIFFERENTLY.
>> AND THE IRONY OF MELO SAYING
THAT, HE D GETO HAVE
THAT, AT LEAST NOT YET.
HAVE YOU TALKED TO HIM ABOUT
THAT?
>> NOT ABOUT THAT.
BUT I'VE WATCHED ONE OF MY
FAVORITE PLAYERS GET PUSHED ■÷÷.
I WATCHED IVERSON PUSHED OUT.
I WATCHED HOW THE GAME CHANGES,
AND HOW QUICKLY THE
ORGANIZATION'S AND THE FAN'S
MIND GOES TO THE NEXT PERSON.
>> AND IT'S BEEN CRAZY.
EARLIER THIS SEASON, WE GOT THE
GREAT MOMENT IN LOS ANGELES,
WITH LeBRON.
VERY MOVING.
NOVAN MITCHELL GIVES YOU A
ROCKING CHAIR.
YOU PLAYEDR LAST IN
MADISON SQUARE GARDEN,■g THE CRD
WENT INSANE FOR YOU.
MVP CHANTS IN THE GARDEN.
THEY CHEERED FOR YOU IN BOSTON,
SOMETHING I THOUGHT I WOULD
NEVER SEE.
DANNY AINGE PRESENTED YOU WITH A
PIECE OF THE PARQUET FLOOR.
>> DID I SCORE ANY BUCKETS ON
THAT FLOOR?
>> A FEW TOO MANY.
WE WEREN'T HAPPY.
>> WHAT'S BEEN THE EXPERIENCE OF
LIVING THROUGH THOSE MOMENTS?
>> IT'S BEEN SURREAL.
IT'S LIKE YOU HAVE THIS VISION
OF HOW YOU WANT THINGS TO GO,
EVERYTHING IN LIFE.
WHEN SOMETHING SURPASSES THAT
VISION, IT'S AN OUT OF BODY
EXPERIENCE.
>> AND THE JERSEY SWAPS HAVE
BECOME THEIR OWN WHOLE SEPARATE
THING.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO WITH
THOSE JERSEYS?
THIS IS A BEAUTIFUL HOUSE.
>> I NEED A SEPARATE MEMORABILIA
HOU SOME POINT.
AT ONE POINT, INT TO GO BACK
AND LOOK AT WHAT WAS SAID, LOOK
AT THE GUYS I PLAYED AGAINST.
I WAS LIKE, WOW, THIS IS COOL,
THIS IS SO DOPE.
YOU KNOW.
>> FOR A LONG TIME, YOU SAID YOU
WANTED TO SPEND YOUR CAREER WITH
MIAMI.
YOU WENT TO CHICAGO, CLEVELAND,
YOU CAME BACK HOME AGAIN.
HOW IS THIS FINAL SWING WITH THE
HEAT DIFFERENT WITH THE FACT
THAT YOU LEFT AND CAME BACK?
>> IT'S DIFFERENT FROM THE
STANDPOINT, WHETHER IT'S ME, THE
ORGANIZATION, THE FAN BASE, WE
UNDERSTAND, WHEN WE DIDN'T HAVE
EACH OTHER, HOW MUCH WE NEEDED
EACH OTHER, AND HOW MUCH WE
APPRECIATED WHAT EVERYBODY
BROUGHT TO THE TABLE.
PEOPLE SAY, I WISH IT NEVER
HAPPENED, BUT IT WAS NEEDED TO.
BECAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU
HAVE UNTIL IT'S GONE.
BUT WE CAME BACK TOGETHER, AND
IT GREAT.
>> A SCA MOMENT THE OTHER DAY
AGAINST MILWAUKEE.
IS THERE A MOMENT IN THE FINAL
STRETCH, THE HANDFUL OF GAMES,
DON'T GET HURT, DON'T GET HURT?
>> YES.
THAT WOULD BE SO -- THAT WOULD
HURT IN A WAY THAT, I WOULD BE
DEPRESSED FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
>> YES.
>> BUT I JUST GO OUT AND PLAY.
I'VE BEEN OUT THERE, AND I'VE
BEEN DOING ALL RIGHT.
>> AS ALWAYS.
SO, THE WAY YOU END THE REGULAR
SEASON, YOU HAVE BACK-TO-BACK, A
HOME GAME AGAINST THE SIXERS,
AND THEN YOU PLAY THE LAST NIGHT
OF THE SEASON UP IN BROOKLYN.
THAT COULD DETERMINE WHETHER YOU
MAKE THE PLAYOFFS OR NOT.
>> YEAH.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THE HOME
GAME, FIRST.
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOUR LAST, AT
LEAST SCHEDULED, HOME GAME IN
MIAMI WILL FEEL LIKE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVE NO IDEA, LIKE, IT'S
TOUGH, RIGHT?
BECAUSE EXACTLY WHAT I DID NOT
WANT TO HAPPEN IS HAPPENING.
I DID NOT WANT TO GO DOWN TO THE
LAST COUPLE OF GAMES AND IT BE
FOR A PLAYOFF SPOT.
SO, THE WAY I PREPARE AND
WILL BE A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
>> YES.
>> BUT FOR ME, IT'S DEFINITELY
GOING TO BE EMOTIONAL.
IT'S THE END OF, LIKE, THE END
OF SOMETHING THAT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
THAT WE'VE BEEN ABLE TO SHARE
TOGETHER.
>> AS WE'RE SITTING HERE IN YOUR
HOUSE, YOU'VE LIVED IN HALF A
DOZPLACES, YOU'VE BEEN AROUND
THE WORLD, YOU'VE DONE THIS,
YOU'VE DONE THAT.
BUT THAT COURT, EVERY YEAR,
SEVERAL TIMES A WEEK, YOU COME
BACK TO THAT COURT.
THAT COURT HAS SEEN YOU GROW UP.
>> YEAH.
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO DO TO ME
RIGHT NOW?
WHAT IS THIS?
>> MAKE YOU CRY, RNOW.
NO, BUT THAT'S KIND OF
■XS MY HOUSE.
I'M IN THAT HOUSE WAY■2■2 THAN ñ
I'M IN THIS HOUSE.
>> THAT'S WHAT I MEAN.
>> IT'S DEFINITELY A BIG PART OF
MY LIFE.
NO ONE WANTS IT TO END.
IT'S BEEN GREAT.
BUT IT HAS TO.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU'RE GOING TO
CRY?
>> I DON'T THINK I'M GOING TO
CRY.
>> YOU WANT TO BET?
>> I DON'T THINK I'M GOING TO
CRY.
I ONLY CRY IN INTIMATE SETTINGS.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THE LAST
GAME UP IN BROOKLYN.
YOU COULD BE VERY WELL GOING
INTO THAT GAME, AND AS THE
MINUTES TICK BY, YOU WON'T KNOW
IF IT'S YOUR LAST GAME.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO THINK ABOUT
IT LIKE THAT.
KOBE HAS SET THIS UNBELLE,
IMPOSSIBLE BAR, PEOPLE FEEL IN
YOUR LAST GAME, YOU HAVE TO
SCORE 60.
WHO DOES THAT?
>> KOBE BRYANT DOES THAT.
>> I'M GOING DO GO OUT THE WAY
D-WADE WILL GO OUT.
IT HELPS THAT WE'RE JUST TRYING
TO WIN, IF IT WASN'T, I WOULD
TRY TO GET 40.
>> IF YOU GO INTO THE GAME,
KNOWING FOR SURE YOU GUYS ARE
OUT OF IT, ARE YOU GOING FOR 40?
>> WELL, I'M GOING TO SHOOT.
A LOT.
WE'LL SEE IF IT GOES IN OR NOT.
>> I WAS THINKING BACK, I'VE
BEEN INTERVIEWING YOU SINCE YOUR
ROOKIE YEAR,ERE BOTH
CHILDREN.
YOU WERE NOT THE CHOSEN ONE, THE
GUY WHO WON MARCH MADNESS.
YOUR PATH WAS NOT LAID OUT FOR
YOU IN THE WAY SOME OF YOUR
FRIENDS' WERE.
HOW DOES IT MAKE IT SWEETER WHAT
YOU'VE ■■ACCOMPLISHED?
>> IT'S MORE OF MES OUT THERE.
THERE ARE ONLY SO MANY LeBRON
JAMES OUT THERE.
BUT THERE'S WAY M DWYANE
HE WORLD.
I WASN'T A McDONALD'S
ALL-AMERICAN, NO CAMPS, I GOT
THREE SCHOLARSHIP OFFERS TO GO
TO COLLEGE.
BUT IT'S A BIG FAMILY TO BE A
PART OF, AND I'M PROUD OF IT.
>> SPEAKING OF THE GUYS WHO
MAYBE HAD A LITTLE BIT MORE JUS.
IT'S BEEN A ROUGH YEAR FOR
LeBRON.
YOU EVER CALL HIM, YOU CAN
RETIRE WITH
>> NO,M■ HE'S FINE.
THE WESTERN CONFERENCE IS NO
JOKE, INJURIES SUCK, HOPEFULLY
HE DOESN'T EXPERIENCE ANY MORE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT'S BEEN IN THE
FINALS EIGHT YEARS IN A ROW.
AT SOME POINT, LIKE, THE
REALIZATION WILL KNOCK YOU IN
THE HEAD.
NOW HE'S GOING TO REFOCUS, HE'LL
BE FINE, THE LAKERS WILL BE
FINE.
I'M NOT CONCERNED WITH LeBRON
JAMES.
HE WILL BE FINE.
>> BY THE WAY, THAT'S ANOTHER
BET WE CAN HAVE.
I KNOW THEIR RELATIVE AGES, BUT
WHO WILL TAP OUT FIRST?
C.P. OR --
>> I KNEW I WAS GOING TO TAP OUT
FIRST.
BUT FOR THOSE GUYS, THEY DON'T
LOOK AT THE END.
C.P. IS STILL CHASING A
CHAMPIONSHIP, TRYING TO GET TO
THE FINALS.
BRON, HE WANTS TO BE LeBRON
JAMES FOREVER.
AND THAT'S THE BATTLE HE WILL
HAVE TO, AS YOU GET OLDER, YOU
HAVE TO FIGHT TO DO THAT.
AND MELO, HE HAS A DIFFERENT
PATH.
HE HAS TO GET BACK IN THIS
LEAGUE.
ALL OF THEM ARE CHASING
DIFFERENT THINGS RIGHT NOW, AND
THEY'RE IN THIS PLACE WHERE
I'M AT.
I'M NOT CHASING ANYTHING.
THAT'S WHY I'M OKAY WALKING FROM
TH BECAUSE EVERY■
WANTED TO CHASE, I ALREADY
GRABBED IT, AND I'VE HAD IT.
NOW I'M LIKE, OKAY, I WANT TO DO
SOMETHING ELSE.
>> SO GOOD.
STAY TUNED, BECAUSE COMING UP,
WE HAVE THE SECOND PART OF THE
CONVERSATION.
WE'LL BE JOINED BY THE BRILLIANT
AND BEAUTIFUL GABRIELLE UNION,
AND THE CUTE BABY.
GABRIELLE TELLS US WHAT MAKES
DWYANE WADE CRY
Don't do it.
Anthony Davis?
Choose Mobil 1
Synthetic instead.
It protects engines better
than conventional motor oil.
You know, you look
much taller on TV.
The camera adds six feet.
Get 250,000 miles
of protection.
Upgrade to Mobil 1.
■■ ■ ■■?5■55■■■■■■■=■=■■■■■=?■■=
♪ There's something
out there ♪
♪ for you and me,  ♪
♪ And the American
road is calling, ♪
♪ so what's it
gonna be? ♪
♪ Hey it's an
amazing day, ♪
♪ Traveling our
own highway, ♪
♪ No matter where
it leads us ♪c
♪ we can smile, ♪
>>> HELLO, BEAUTY.
>> HE'S NOT GOING TO CRY ABOUT
THAT.
YOU'RE ASKING THE WRONG
QUESTION.
THE SECRET TO HIS TEARS?
MARLEY AND ME.
>> I HAD SOMETHING IN MY EYE.
I COULDN'T GET IT OUT.
>> WE READ THE BOOK FIRST,
TOGETHER.
YOU CRIED.
AND THEN THE MOVIE CAME OUT, AND
>> MY EYES GOT A LITTLE MOIST.
>> THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
WHAT DO YOU THINK HE WILL MISS
THE MOST ABOUT PLAYING IN THE
NBA?
>> OH, HIS FRIENDS.
HIS FRIENDS.
>> DO YOU THINK IT WILL BE WEIRD
FOR HIM THAT THOSE GUYS YOU
MENTIONED WILL ALL STILL BE
PLAYING, AND HE'S GOING TO BE
SITTING ON THE COUCH?
>> DOING THIS?
>> I'M SURE THERE WILL BE TIMES
WHERE HE ISNG TO, YOU KNOW,
START TO DISSECT THE GAME.
THIS IS WHAT I WOULD HAVE DONE.
BUT WE'LL FIND OUT, RIGHT?
I'M SURE TWITTER WILL KNOW IF HE
IS LIKE, YOU KNOW --
>> YOU GOT SOMETHING YOU WANT TO
SAY?
>> YOU THINK HE WILL BE A HATER,
HE WILL TURN INTO A HATER?
>> NO.
>> IT'S WEIRD WHEN PROFESSIONAL
ATHLETES RETIRE.
YOU'RE NOT JUST QUITTING YOUR
JOB.
THIS HAS DICTATED WHAT CITY YOU
LIVE IN, WHEN YOU GO ON
VACATION, WHEN YOU EAT, WHEN YOU
GO TO SLEEP AND WAKE UP.
WHAT DO YOU THINK THAT WILL BE
LIKE?
>> I WILL BE IN THERAPY.
NO, SERIOUSLY.
>> OKAY.
>> IT WILL BE A BIG CHANGE.
I TOLD MY WIFE, I NEED TO DO
THERAPY, WE NEED TO DO A LITTLE
BIT.
I WAS ALWAYS AGAINST SOMEONE
THAT DON'T KNOW TELLING ME HOW
TO LIVE MY LIFE, BUT I NEED
SOMEBODY TO TALK TO ABOUT IT.
I HAVE A LONG LIFE TO LIVE, AND
THERE ARE OTHER GREAT THINGS TO
ACCOMPLISH AND DO, IT'S NOT
THIS.
SO, IT WILL BE DIFFERENT.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT WILL MAKE
IT OKAY FOR OTHER PEOPLE DO
THAT?
>> I'VE BEEN GOING MANY YEARS.
HE'S LIKE, OKAY, GOOD LUCK WITH
THAT.
SO, FOR HIM TO COME AROUND AND
SEE THE BENEFITS AND LOOK
FORWARD TO IT, IT WILL DO A LOT
FOR THE STIGMA.
YOU KNOW, MIND, BODY, AND SOUL
WELLNESS.
>> AND OTHER PEOPLE DO A LOT OF
STUFF FOR YOU WHEN YOU'RE A
PROFESSIONAL ATHLETE.
WHAT WILL HE BE THE MOST A MESS
ABOUT?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF HE'LL CHANGE
THAT A LOT.
>> STOP THAT TALK.
LISTEN.
>> THANK GOD, THE MAN HAS
INVESTED WELL.
HE'S DONE QUITE WELL FOR
HIMSELF.
>> WE'RE MOVING, NOT MOVING, BUT
WE'LL SPEND MORE TIME IN L.A.
AND JUST A FEW THINGS THAT I'VE
HAD IN MY MIND, TO MAKE AN
ADJUSTMENT TO.
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> LIKE, NEW SHEETS EVERY DAY IN
MY BED.
CLEAN TOWELS EVERY DAY.
>> WE'RE ON THE BLACK ACTRESS
SALARY IN L.A., AND NOW THAT THE
ME IN LOS ANGELES, WE'LL HAVE A
ROMANTIC DIP IN THE POOL, HE'S
LOOKING UNDERNEATH, AND HE WROTE
A STRONGLY WORDED EMAIL TO THE
GROUNDSKEEPER.
AM I LYING?
>> BECAUSE IT WAS MOLDY OR
SOMETHING?
>> THERE WERE LEAVES.
IT'S OUTSIDE.
LEAVES HAPPEN.
>> IN ADDITION TO YOUR FUTURE
LANDSCAPING CAREER, YOU'RE
ALREADY A WINE MAKER, A SOCK,
CLOTHES, AND SHOE MAGNATE.
ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT GOING
INTO BROADCASTING?
I NEED HIM ON THE SET OF "THE
JUMP."
SE I LOVE YRGUMENT TO
TRACY McGRADY.
AND I NEED HELP, BECAUSE HE WINS
EVERYTHING.
YOU NEED TO COME HELP ME.
CAN WE WORK THIS OUT?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT IT IS
THAT I WANT TO DO YET.
BUT I KNOW I WANT TO DO A LITTLE
BIT OF EVERYTHING.
ESPECIALLY IN THE BEGINNING.
I WANT TO SEE WHAT I CAN BE
GREAT AT.
I'M SO USED TO BEING GREAT AT
SOMETHING, OR TRYING TO STRIVE
TO BE GREAT AT SOMETHING.
SO, WE'LL SEE.
>> WHAT IS THE THING THAT YOU
AND THE KIDS ARE THE MOST
EXCITED HE'S GOING TO BE AROUND
FOR NEXT?
>> JUST THE REGULAR DUMB LITTLE
THINGS.
TRIPS TO THE VET.
>> HE'S LIKE, I DON'T HAVE TO DO
THAT.
>> HAVE YOU EVER BEEN TO THE
VET?
WE HAVE FIVE DOGS.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN TO THE VET
IN.
>> NO.
>> WE TALKED ABOUT YOUR CAREER,
AND YOUR LEGACY IS SO MUCH MORE
THAN POINTS AND ASSISTS.
YOU, LeBRON, AND CHRIS CHANGED
THE COURSE OF THE NBA, WITH THE
WAY ■pERS HAGENCY.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN TO YOU?
>> IT MEANS A LOT, WHETHER TO
THE GENERATION TO COME, THAT
WILL NOT EVEN KNOW WHO I AM.
BUT IT MEANS A LOT TO BE A PART
OF HELPING PLAYERS UNDERSTAND
THEIR POWER.
AS WE'VE LEARNED OVER THE YEARS.
AND I HOPE I'VE SET A GOOD
ENOUGH EXAMPLE FOR WHO IS TO
COME NEXT.
TO UNDERSTAND THE POWER, TO
UNDERSTAND THE VOICE, HOW TO USE
THIS PLATFORM.
I MADE A LOT OF MISTAKES BEFORE
I GOT HERE, SO HOPEFULLY WE CAN
HELP THE NEXT GENERATION.
>> WHEN YOU PUT ON THE HOODIES
FOR TRAYVON MARTIN, IT HAD BEEN
DECADES SINCE SOMETHING LIKE
THAT HAPPENED.
>> WHEN I READ ARTICLES, SO AND
SO LED THE WAY FOR FASHION, HE'S
BEEN AT THE FOREFRONT.
BETTING ON HIMSELF, NOW HAVING A
LIFETIME DEAL.
YES, MY DADDY DID THAT.
PEOPLE THOUGHT HE WAS CRAZY.
AND HE'S NEVER BEEN ONE, HE'D
RATHER TAKE THE RISK AND BET ON
HIMSELF.
AND I THINK THAT SORT OF, I
DON'T KNOW.
THAT SENSE OF HAVING A GREAT
SENSE OF SELF, KNOWING EXACTLY
WHAT YOUR VALUE AND WORTH IS.
>> AND BEING BULLHEADED.
WHATEVER TERM WE WANT TO USE.
>> LAST SUMMER, I WOULD CHECK IN
WITH YOU, AND SAY, OH, COME ON,
YOU'RE NOT REALLY DONE.
WHEN I TEXT YOU, ARE YOU REALLY
DONE, THIS ■@■@MMER?
WHAT WIL BE?
>> IT WILL BE A PHOTO OF US ON
VACATION, A COUPLE DRINKS.
NONE OF THAT TRAINING CRAZINESS.
BUT I'M IN A GOOD PLACE.
I'M IN A REAL GOOD SPACE, AND I
HAVEN'T BEEN IN THAT SPACE FOR A
LONG TIME.
SO, I'M HAPPY WITH HOW MY BODY
FEELS, I'M HAPPY WITH THE EXTRA
ITIONS TO MY LIFE.
AND I'M EXCITED ABOUT THE
UNKNOWN.X
HOW WWE GET IT D
SO■T■T
■T■@  EXCIT7@UT IT.
>>7KS TNTIRE
FAMILY FOR WEING US INTO  LLY
D WEVER THE Y■■ NICE AL W■■■
F■■TOO.■■■■■■■■ROAT TOGETHLOT O.
TRACY, WHEN■ YOU LISTEN TO DWYAE
WADE, DO YOU FEEL LIKE HE'S
READY TO RETIRE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IT WAS A CLIFF, HE JUST GOT
TIRED OF GOING TO SHOOTAROUNDS,
GOING TO PRACTICE.
HE DIDN'T LOOK FORWARD TO THAT.
I CAN RELATE TO THAT, BECAUSE
PRA■■SHOOTARS,THINGS ■
■■■■■■■ NATURE, TIME TO HANG IT
UP.
>> THE CLEVELAND/DETROIT/PHILLY
TRIPS IN THE WINTER.
AND HE'S PUT A LOT OF THOUGHT
INTO THIS.
THE TEAM HASN'T PERFORMED LIKE
HE WANTED IT TO THIS SEASON, BUT
HE'S WON THE REGULAR SEASON, HAS
BEEN THERE EVERY NIGHT WITH JOY,
HE'S HAD GREAT MOMENTS.
EVEN ON BAD NIGHTS, GREAT JOY.
WHAT HE'S DONE, I WOULDN'T■■■■1■
■■■■77    ■■■■■■■MS NEXTEAR CHU
YEAR.OOOD THIS ■■■■
■LDN'T 100% RULE IT OUT.
WITH DONE.
■ES I ■■■■■
■■.
>> DID■■/■■■ SEE THE■/■/E HAS?
>> T G■■■■E/E/E/■■■■■■■■■C■■■ K■
>> WE'
MENTAL HEALTH, WE'VE SEEN
PLAYERS WALK AWAY FROM THE GAME,
HAPPY, SUCCESSFUL PLAYERS, DO IT
BY THEIR CHOICE, HAVING TO DEAL
WITH LOSING ALL THE STRUCTURE IN
THEIR LIFE.
GOING THROUGH DEPRESSION, HAVING
A HARD TIME■■ WITH ■■■■■■■■■■■■
■■■AKE IT WORK,■/■■■■■ BE■■AWES
A HUGE PART OF THE LEGACY WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>>> LET'S GET TO WHAT "THE JUMP"
RECOMMENDS.
LET'S GO OVER TO THE HOUSTON
ROCKETS YOUTUBE PAGE.
I LOVED THIS.
I RECOMMEND ALL OF YOU SIT DOWN,
WHERE AMAZING HAPPENED, THE
STORY OF THE 2007/2008 ROCKETS.
TRACY, WHAT WAS YOUR FAVORITE
MOMENT?
>> JUST GOING THROUGH IT WITH
THOSE GUYS THAT WE HAD.
THE CAMARADERIE THAT WE FORMED.
AND WITH ALL THE MEDIA ■á
IT WAS LIKE WE WERE ON VE,
AMPIONSHIP ONE.
>> 22-GAME WINSTREAK.
AS AWESOME.
>>ABSOLUTEL■E MISSED I LIVE IN ,
CHECK IT OUT LIVE ON THE RO■á
Tanner again from downtown!
like everyone is
night.own, Ken.@oo■■? ■■■■■■■r
Ordered three of those small
plates, that was not enough.
So then I got nine, and that was
too much.
Well you know, I paid for it, so
I ate it all.
Just OK is not OK.
Whether it's announcers or
wireless networks.
AT&T is America's best wireless
network,
according to America's biggest
test.
Now with 5G Evolution, the first
step to 5G.
MORE FOR YOU THAT'S OUR
THING.
>>> HAND DOWN, MAN DOWN.
>> BOYS, BRING IT IN.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO NEED A LOT
MORE HELP THAN THAT, FELLAS.
>> WHEN YOU NEED A POWER-UP ON
THE COURT, JUST SAY THE WORD.
>> SHAZAM!
>> I THINK WE'LL STICK TO
TWO-ON-TWO, FELLAS.
>> LET'S RUN IT BACK.
LAY ET'S RUN IT BACK.
CHECKERS?
>> NO.
>> TONIGHT ON "SPORTSCENTER,"
COLLEGE GAMEDAY'S FINAL FOUR
PREDICTIONS.
AND MEL KIPER JR. ONHE DRAFT
PLUS, MUCH MORE ON RACHEL
NICHOLS' CONVERSATION WITH
DWYANE WA■2D)D)
"SPORTSCENTER," RIGHT
AFTER "PTI".
>>> NBA FRIDAY DOUBLE-HEADER,
THANK YOU, BY THE WAY,■úp■
ENTER."
CELTICS/PACERS, 8:00 P.M.
EASTERN.
THEN, THIS IS A HUGE SEEDING
MATCHUP.
BLAZERS/NUGGETS.
"NBA COUNTDOWN,"■■■ ■  7P.M.,
ESPN, THE SHOW WILL GET ■■■■■■
READY FOR EVERYTHING TONIG
LET'S TALK ABOUT BOSTON AND
INDY.
THEY HAVE THE SAME ■ECORD,
JOSTLING TO■■■■■■■■ ■
ADVANTAGE.■■ NEEDS HOME COURT M?
>> LAST YEAR, THE PACERS, IN THE
FIRST ROUND,■&?&■&■,■# TO PLAY
USTASED ON THAT, )■)■)■)■)■)■h■a
REGARDLESS OF THEIR MATCHUP, I
THINK THEY'D LIKE TO HAVE GAME
SEVEN AT HOME THIS YEAR.
AND BOSTON IS A LITTLE BIT
VULNERABLE.
>> WHOEVER WINS THIS GAME.
>> YOU'RE WITH WHOEVER WINS THE
GAME?
>> WHOEVER WINS THIS GAME.
■@ ARE READY, THEY KNOW  IT SHO
WHAT'S AT STAKE.
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE HORFORD,
HE MIGHT BE OUT.
BROWN WILL BE OUT, AND MORRIS
MAY BE OUT.
THREE OF THEIR KEY GUYS OUT FOR
TONIGHT.
IF THEY CAN GO TO INDIANA AND
WIN THIS GAME, THAT WET■■ ME
KNOW WHERE THEY■■■■■■■■■■■■ñ■ç
A OF YOU HAVE SEEN
RICHARD JEFFERSON DO HIS
BREAKDOWN■I/■■■■N WHAT HE WOULDW
TO THE CELTICS PLAYER TO■■Q■QWO.
BECAUSE R.J. IS■ A MASTER.
AND BOSTON, HARD DROPPING
POINTS OFF THE BENCH.
GOINE 13 TIMES.
HIS MOST AS A CELTIC.
HERE'S WHAT KYRIE IRVING SAID
AFTER THE GAME.
WE'RE BEST WHEN HE'S LOOKING FOR
HIS SHOT.
HE'S A GREAT FACILITATOR, BUT WE
NEED "G" TO SCORE.
I'VE TOLD HIM THAT, TO BE HIM,
STAY AGGRESSIVE, AND BE THE
■INTRER THAT HE WAS.
YO■s S LIKE TO COME
BACK FROM A HUGE RY.
AND GORDON SAID HE FEELS LIKE
HE'S NOT HIMSELF.  NOT LAT, BUT
>> DOH FEELING,
YRIE SAYS, JUST BE THE GUYOU
USED TO BE.
IT'S NOT THAT EASY, RIGHT?
>> AT THE END OF TON, I
CAN UNDERSTAND, HIMTRYING TO
FEEL HIS WAY IN.
WE'RE AT■ ■@■@■@■@■@■ H■ ■
EXTREMELYCONFIDENT, AND HE
NEEDS TO BE AGGRESSI
HE NEEDS TO BE THAT 20-POINT ■ .
HE'S CAPABLE OF DOING THAT, HE
HAS  FOR HIS SHOTS.
>> THE BIG WIN IN MIAMI, THEY
WENT DOWN.
AND YOK■■W[■■■E THROWS.
THAT WAS ANALL-STAR IN■UTA■ ME~/
>> THE SECOND PART OF THE ■
D-■■■■W■W■W■W■W■W■W■W■W■W■; Y■;
HE WILL BE BACK TO NORMAL ONCE
HIS RECOVERY IS OVER.
HE SAID I THINK IT'S DISCOMFORT.
IF I'M READY BEFORE THE
■÷ I DON'TI'LL BE BACK.
TUNE-UP GAME, I'VE BEEN THERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> HE'S A VET.
HE'S NOT A GUY THAT PLAYS ABOVE
THE RIM.
HE'S A SHOOTER.
HE'S B■W■W■í#T OFF OF QUICKNESS.
HE'S JUST A CEREBRAL PLAYER, AND
I THINK HE WILL BE FINE.
PORTLAND HAS BEEN FINE WITHOUT
HIM, 9-1, IN■&■&■&■&■&■&■&■&ABS.
HICK, I  WILL
BEPLUS.
FIND HIS RHYTHM RIGHT AWAY,
BECAUSE HE'S THAT TYPE OF
PLAYER.
>> I'M GOING TO TRY TO TRANSLATE
THAT QUOTE.
HE■E■[ITE ■
DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE
GAME,
Y.
NCE.
SO IMPRESSED WITH THE ■Q
BLAZERS■Q■[LEADERSHIP OF
DAMIAN LILLARD.
>>> COMING UP, LeBRON JAMES
NIGHT'S GAME.FT
IS THIS A SIGN OF THINGS TO
COME?
I DON'T KNOW.
RST,■8 THEANT REPLAY
FROM THISI■DATE  2005.■■x
SHOUT-OUT, SHAWN7w■■pYpY8O■v■LI.
HE WAS RELEASED FROM THREE
SEPARATE TEAMS ON CHRISTMAS WEEK
EACH TIME, BECAUS
♪♪D ■ D
♪♪
úúú ♪ Orange
Vanilla Coke ♪
♪ Yeah, you heard
that right! ♪
Don't do it.
Anthony Davis?
Choose Mobil 1
Synthetic instead.
It protects engines better
than conventional motor oil.
You know, you look
much taller on TV.
The camera adds six feet.
Get 250,000 miles
of protection.
Upgrade to Mobil 1.
Reese's eggs are back
and we hid them
somewhere you'll never find...
Sike! We put them everywhere.
Grocery stores and
supermarkets, gas stations,
which we already mentioned...
Basketball in its purest form.
♪♪
Grocery stores and
supermarkets, gas stations,
This is 3X3U.
Man: Samson moves in,
Tate -- Oh, my goodness!
That was nastier than
toothpaste and orange juice!
One basket
on a single ha.
Seniors from around the nation.
Three-on-three basketball
with one substitution
so you can -- ooh! --
catch your breath.
We're checking the ball
from the country's largest mall,
and we're gonna crown a champion
with 100 large.
(Ariana)
What is he DOING?
hú(Vince)
He better not be messing up
our taxes.
(Lisa)
At H&R Block, you have your own
screen so you can see your
credits, deductions and tax
tips!
(Vince)
We need that now.
(Tax Pro)
What?
(Lisa VO) ♪
Know as you go at
H&R Block.
See your credits, deductions
and tax tips.
Block has your back.
So I can buy from
■■■>Q&Q&Q&Q&
Enterprise Car Sales and you'll
NY trade-in?
That's right!
Great!
Here you go...
Well, it does need
to be a vehicle.
But - I need this out of
my house.
(VO) With fair, transparent
value for every trade-in...
Enterprise makes it easy.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
"DETAIL," FROM THE MIND OF KOBE
BRYANT.
AVAILABLE RIGHT NOW ON ESPN D&&W
IT'S CRUNCH TIME HERE ON "THE
JUMP."
FORMER NBA STAR JERRY
STACKHOUSE, IF IOULD CLAP WITH
THIS BROKEN HAND, IWOULD.
RED ASññ BAA
OACH AT■■■■2 VLT UNIVERSITY.#÷
T-MA■n WHAT DO YOU REMEMBER MO■c
ABOUT STACK?
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO PLAY
AGAINST HIM.
IN HIGH SCHOOL, STACK, I USED TO
OUT WITH HIM IN NORTH
CAROLINA.
>> VERY NICE.
I LIKE THAT.
FANTASTIC COACHING CAREER HE'S
BUD HIMSEL
>> AND HE MAY BE COACHING
SCOTTIEPIPSON.
WE'LL SEE IF HE CAN KEEP HIM.
I WANT TO DISCUSS AN INTERESTING
MO■ú BETWEEN LeBRON JAMES AND
K.D. AT THE STAPLES CENTER LAST
NIGHT.
THEY SHARED A COUPLE OF SECRET
WORDS.
K.D., OBVIOUSLY, THE MOSTpp8@8@h
FREE AGENT ON THE MARKET THIS
SUMMER.
>> KNOW THEY'RE GOING TO  I■yp■p
TALK ABOUT THIS ON ALL THE
TELECASTS.
>> OKAY, NOW WE'RE DON
>> aEVERYONK■4■h■p■4■p■g■p■h■h■
THE "THIS" IN BASKETBALL, RIGHT?
>> THERE ARE TWO WAY
TH
TMOUT PUT THE EL
.
>> HE'S BEENCING THIS F■ga@■■■
STARTED DOINGIT.
>> WHEN HE■X■X■XOKE TONZO%
>> WE WERE DOING THIS ON THE O■,
BENCH ALL THE TIME.
>> YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT OTHER
THINGS.
LEAGUE PASS GAME OF THE NIGHT,
LAKERS AT CLIPPERS.
THE LAKERS AREH■H■ H
PLANE, TRAVELING ALL THE WAY TO
THEIR OWN ARENA.
ZUBAC SAID, IF YOU WANT TO WATCH
PLAYOFF BASKETBALL, WATCH THIS
GAME.
WHICH FRANCHISE WOULD YOU BUY
■■■■TUR■■■> THIS IS NOT A■@■■■W
ANSWER, IT'S A STEVE BALLMER
ANSWER.
IT'S THE LAKERS.
>> HE MADE, WHAT, $40 BILLION?
I'M BUYING THAT STOCK.
>> THEY HAVE GREAT
INFRASTRUC■
ASRE, THE CLIPPERS■I
NO LONGER AéHING■@
■GOING WITH STABILITY OVER
INSTABILITY.
>> WE HAVE A QUICK SURPRISE FOR
YOU BRIAN.
ROLLING NOW, GO.
>> SELL!
SELL!
OH.■■■■@1■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■)■).
I DON'T KNOW WHY WE NEVER ENDED
UP FINISHING, IS IT BECAUSE YOU
DIDN'T LIKE --
>> THAT WA■CT■@IS STILL IN íX
LOPMENT.
Y DID■u WE AIR, IT SAYS■, NOT
?
>> AN■■[okDAYKk STEPHEN■cEúY ■@Y
g8@=