DIDN'T LIKE --
>> THAT WA■CT■@IS STILL IN íX
LOPMENT.
Y DID■u WE AIR, IT SAYS■, NOT
?
>> AN■■[okDAYKk STEPHEN■cEúY ■@Y
g8@=u■uAu■u■Cu OUpuER.
TIME.AR ABOUTCua=■= ALL■b■ THE
HE'SENIOR MONOLOGUE
PRODUCER, HE CREATED",■,■,■I■,■
AY, ALL THE RUN I BACKS,
ARE
[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
ESPN, INC.]
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VISIT NCICAP.ORG]
BOMANI: I AM SO CONFUSED.
I CAN'T FIND THE YEAR.
PABLO: WHAT YEAR ARE WE TALKING
ABOUT?
BOMANI: THE YEAR YOU WON.
THEY ONLY GIVE THOSE TO YOU IF
YOU WON.
ARE YOU A MEMBER?
PABLO: I GET I IS NEXT WEEK.
THANK■QQ■ GET IT.
BOMANI: NO, NO, NO.
I FEEL LIKE IF YOU ARE A
MEMBER, THAT IS A REALLY BIG
DEAL.
PABLO: I WORE THE COAT TODAY
BECAUSE I KNEW I COULDN'T WEAR
IT NEXT WEEK.
YOU WOULD HAVE MADE FUN OF ME.
BOMANI: ARE YOU THE FIRST■■■
FILIPINO TO JOIN AUGUSTA
NATIONAL?
PABLO: FIRST NAME, THE BUCKS.
MILWAUKEE CLINCHED THE BEST
RECORD IN THE LEAGUE, SECURING
HOME COURT IN THE PLAYOFFS.
GIANNIS HAT 45-13-6-5 AND THEY
DID IT WITHOUT ONE ERIC
BLEDSOE, WHO GOT ELI JECTED
LESS THAN -- EJECTED LESS THAN
THREE MINUTES INTO THE GAME.
LET'S WATCH HOW THAT HAPPENED.
[LAUGHTER]
BOMANI: IT IS THE REACTION TIME
THAT MADE IT SO AMAZING.
PABLO: RIGHT AWAY.
BLEDSOE DIDN'T WANT TO BE HERE,
IT SEEMS BECAUSE THIS HAPPENED
SO IMMEDIATELY.
BOMANI: I DON'T THINK THAT WAS
EJECTION-WORTHY.
PABLO: IF YOU ARE THROWING A
BASKETBALL AT SOMEONE, MAYBE HE
THINKS LET ME GET OUT AHEAD OF
THIS.
BOMANI: HE GOT THROWN AT FIRST.
ERIC BLEDSOE, STAY READY.
PABLO: YES.
BO, THIS WAS SOMETHING OF A
STATEMENT WIN FOR THE BUCKS
LAST NIGHT, WAS IT NOT?
BOMANI: THE SIXERS DON'T HAVE
BUTLER BRLT, BUT MIROTIC IS NOT
PLAYING FOR THE BUCKS.
MALCOLM BROGDON IS STILL NOT
BACK FOR THE BUCKS.
WHAT BUCKS TEAM WE GET IN THE
FIRST ROUND IS NOT GOING TO BE
THE SAME TEAM WE GET IN THE
SECOND ROUND IF THEY ARE THERE.
THESE ARE TWO LEGITIMATE CON
DENIEDERS, AND THE BUCKS WENT
THIS THERE AND WON IT LATE.
THIS WASN'T JUST SMOOTH
SAILING.
THEY WERE DOWN LATE AND PULLED
IT OUT AT THE END.
PABLO: GIANNIS KILLED THE
SIXERS THE THE OTHER TWO GAMES,
32-189-10, AND 52-16-7.
LAST NIGHT IN SPECIFIC WE SAW
HIM BLOCK JOEL EMBIID FOUR
TEAMS.
EMBIID HAS NEVER BEEN BLOCKED
SO MANY TIMES BY A SINGLE
PLAYER.
WE SAW HIM DO THAT TO EMBIID.
WE SAW HIM PUT HIS SHOULDER
INTO SIMMONS SIMMONS OTHER AND
OVER AGAIN AND BACK HIM DOWN.
BUTLER OR NOT, ANTETOKOUNMPO
SEEMS TO BE A NIGHTMARE MATCH
UP FOR THE SIXERS.
BOMANI: SIMMONS TOOK FIVE OR
SIX SHOTS.
WHAT MAKES US INTRIGUED ABOUT
THE SIXERS?
THEY HAVE ONE OF THE BEST
STARTING FIVES IN THE NBA.
IT IS THOSE TWO GUYS RIGHT NOW,
SIMMONS AND EMBIID, THE
PROCESS.
THAT IS WHAT EVERYBODY IS
EXCITED ABOUT.
WHEN YOU SEE EMBIID PLAY
AGAINST GUYS OF SIMILAR SIZE,
THEY BRING IT RIGHT BACK TO
HIM, AND THAT IS MORE THAN AT
TIMES HE IS ABLE TO HANDLE.
THIS POSTSEASON IS GOING TO BE
A FASCINATING REFERENDUM ON
WHAT THE SIXERS OR AND ARE NOT.
PABLO: THEY HAVE A COACH TASKED
WITH UNLOCKING THE MOST
TALENTED STARTING FIVE AS YOU
MENTIONED, AND BRETT BROWN HAS
NOT PASSED WITH FLYING COLORS.
MAYBE HE HAS A GUY WHO CAN'T
SHOOT THAT NOBODY ELSE IN THE
EASTERN CONFERENCE FEARS IN THE
POSTSEASON IN BEN SIMMONS.
THAT IS TRUE.
BUT IN THE MILWAUKEE BUCKS,
THEY HAVE A COACH IN MIKE
BUDENHOLZER, WHO HAS UNLOCK THE
AN OFFENSE IN WAYS THAT IS
COACH OF THE YEAR WORTHY AND
THAT MUST MAKE OTHER TEAMS
JEALOUS AS WELL.
BOMANI: IN THE END, YOU GRIND
DOWN, AND YOU NEED GUYS TO GET
THEIR OWN SHOT.
HOW MANY SHOTS CAN GIANNIS GET
FOR HIMSELF AND OTHER PEOPLE.
THAT IS THE QUESTION.
YOU MENTIONED BRETT BROWN.
HE WENT BE AROUND NEXT YEAR.
PABLO: IF AL HORFORD MURDERS
BRETT BROWN, I WOULD HAVE TO
SAY I GET IT.
BOMANI: THE FINAL FOUR.
AUBURN TAKES ON VIRGINIA, AND
TEXAS TECH STATES ON MICHIGAN
STATE FOR THE RIGHT TO PLAY IN
THE NCAA CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
THERE IS NO ZION.
DOES THAT SUCK THE OXYGEN OUT
OF THE TOURNAMENT?
PABLO: I AM GOING TO SAY IT IS
NICE FOR VIRGINIA, TEXAS TECH,
AUBURN AND ONE OTHER.
IF THEY COUNTERED THIS FINAL
FOUR WITH CAMERA IN THE GYM
THAT ZION WILLIAMSON IS PLAYING
IN, WHAT WU BE WATCH SOMETHING
I WOULD BE WATCHING ZION
WILLIAMSON.
BOMANI: THE THING THEY HAVE GOT
HERE IS THIS SHOULD BE GOOD
BASKETBALL.
WE HAD AS GOOD AN ELITE EIGHT
WEEKEND AS WE CAN REMEMBER
THERE BEING.
TEXAS TECH IS ACTUALLY PRETTY
FUN TO WATCH.
THEY ARE WELL COACHED.
THE BALL MOVES AND THEY PLAY
GOOD DEFENSE.
VIRGINIA, I WOULD RATHER DRAWN
MYSELF, BUT THEY HAVE A PRETTY
GOOD GAME.
AUBURN CAN GET UP AND DOWN THE
FLOOR.
MICHIGAN STATE, IF THERE IS ONE
PLAYER WE POINT TO, IT IS THEY
HAVE IN CASSIUS WINSTON.
IF YOU STUMBLE UPON THESE
GAMES.
I THINK YOU ARE GOING TO GET
VERY GOOD BASKETBALL.
BUT UNLESS YOU STUMBLE ACROSS
IT, YOU DON'T HAVE A REASON TO
GO OUT OF YOUR WAY TO SEE THIS,
IF YOU ARE NOT A BIG COLLEGE
BASKETBALL FAN.
PABLO: YOU MENTIONED THAT YOU
WOULD RATHER DROWN YOURSELF
THAN WATCHING THEM.
VIRGINIA PLAYS BASKETBALL LIKE
THEY ARE TRYING TO DROWN
THEMSELVES AND THEIR OPPONENT.
IN TERMS OF TEMPO THEY ARE
353RD IN THE COUNT.
BOMANI: OUT OF HOME?
PABLO: I DON'T KNOW.
BOMANI: 353.
PABLO: THAT MAKES SENSE.
TEXAS TECH IS EXCELLENT.
THEY HAVE IN JARRETT CULVER
POTENTIALLY A TOP FIVE PICK.
THEY HAVE A DEFENSE.
IN THE DATABASE, THEY ARE THE
BEST DEFENSE HE HAS EVER SEEN.
NOW WHAT DOES THAT DO FOR THE
GENERAL AUDIENCE?
WHAT DOES IT DO WHEN MICHIGAN
STATE IS OUT THERE AND TOM IZZO
IS THE BIGGEST NAME, AND BRUCE
PEARL IS OUT THERE, AND HE IS
THE BIGGEST NAME FOR AUBURN.
WHAT IF AUBURN WINS THIS?
THAT IS KIND OF WHAT I AM
ROOTING FOR PURELY FOR THE
SIGHT OF MARK EMMERT HANDING
SOME SOME TROPHY TO THAT GIO.
BOMANI: AND ME GOING OWE WAS,
BRUCE PEARL.
IT IS HARD FOR ME TO FIND NICE
THINGS TO SAY.
CAN WE TALK ABOUT ZION?
WE DID HAVE THE OPTION OF
TALKING ABOUT OTHER GUYS.
WE JUST NEVER DID.
WE HAD ONE GUY, AND WE LIKED
IT.
THAT IS WHY WE DON'T KNOW WHO
THE HELL ANYBODY ELSE IS
COLLEGE BASKETBALL.
BASEBALL WE HAVE NEVER BEEN SO
UNINTERESTED IN OTHER THAN
PEOPLE.
OUR LAST NAME, MUFFET MCGRAW.
SHE SAID SHE HAS NO PLANS TO
HIRE A MALE COACH AT ANY POINT
IN THE FUTURE.
YESTERDAY, MCGRAW WAS ASKED
ABOUT THIS AT THE FINAL FOUR.
LET'S LISTEN TO HER.
>> THIS IS A PATH FOR YOU TO
TAKE TO GET TO THE POINT WHERE
IN THIS COUNTRY WE HAVE 50% OF
WOMEN IN POWER, WE HAVE LIGHT
-- RIGHT NOW LESS THAN 5% OF
WOMEN ARE C.E.O.'S OF FORTUNE
500 COMPANIES.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT MEN'S
BASKETBALL, AND THE 989% OF THE
JOBS GO TO MEN.
WHY SHOULDN'T 99% OR 100% OF
THE WOMEN'S JOBS GO TO WOMEN?
MAYBE BECAUSE WE ONLY HAVE 10
ATHLETIC DIRECTORS IN
TELEVISION DIVISION I.
PEOPLE HIRE PEOPLE WHO LOOK
LIKE THEM, AND THAT IS THE
PROBLEM.
PABLO: BO, WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF
THAT?
BOMANI: THAT LAST POINT, I
DON'T THINK IT IS THAT AS MUCH
AS THEY HIRE ON PEOPLE WHO THEY
THINK IS BETTER ON SUPERFICIAL
TERMS.
YOU SEE IT IN AFRICAN SOCCER.
ALL THOSE AFRICAN TEAMS HIRE
WHITE COACHES.
THEY ARE SUBSCRIBING LAZYLY TO
THE IDEA THAT THE PRIVILEGED
CLASS IS BETTER AT THIS JOB
THAN OTHERS.
IT IS HARD TO ARGUE WITH WHAT
SHE SAID.
YOU SEE FINAL FOUR, FINAL FOUR,
FINAL FOUR, AND OVER AND OVER
AGAIN HERE.
UNLESS WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
SOMEBODY NOT HIRING QUALIFIED
PEOPLE, THEN THERE IS NOTHING
REALLY TO BE MAD AT.
INSTEAD, TAKE HOLD OF THE
NUMBERS SHE WAS GIVING THERE.
DAN LE BATARD WAS TALKING
BETWEEN.
WHEN EDDIE MURPHY DID HIS
MOVIES, HE HAD BLACK PEOPLE
HOLDING CAMERAS AND EVERYTHING
ELSE.
NOBODY ELSE WAS GOING TO BE ONE
TO DO.
SHE HAS DECIDED THAT, AND I
DON'T BLAME HER ABOUT IT.
PABLO: THERE IS A COUNTER
ARGUMENT BASED IN THE IDEA THAT
THIS JUST MEANS YOU ARE GOING
TO HIGH ANYBODY BUT A WHITE
MAN, AND DOESN'T THAT CALL INTO
QUESTION CERTAIN THINGS LIKE
ILLEGAL HIRING?
IT IS DISCRIMINATORY.
IT IS ILLEGAL WHAT MUFFET
MCGRAW SAID, BUT WHEN YOU TAKE
IT IN CONTEXT, AN ENTERTAINER
SAID HE IS NOT GOING TO HIRE A
WHITE LEAD FOR HIS MOVIES
BECAUSE ONE OF THE PROBLEMS
THAT HAS EMERGED IS A LANDSCAPE
THAT DOES NOT HAVE AN EQUALITY
OF OUTCOME.
IT IS SHAKING OUT WHERE IN
WOMEN'S BASKETBALL, THE WOMEN
HAVE A CERTAIN PRESENCE, AND IN
MEN'S BASKETBALL, THEY HAVE
NEXT TO NONE.
WHAT DO THE WOMEN DO IF NOT
FENLED FOR THEMSELVES?
BOMANI: RIGHT.
THIS HAPPENS WHEN YOU WIN HOW
SHE HAS WON.
YOU GET A MEASURE OF PEOPLE TO
BE OIBLE TO DO THESE SORTS OF
THINGS.
I DON'T THINK ANYBODY CAN MAKE
AN ARGUMENT THAT THIS IS OUT OF
MALICE OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
THIS IS NOT A MATTER OF OF
SCRAME NATURING AGAINST MEN
NEARLY AS MUCH AS IT IS
EMPOWERING WOMEN.
THE FLIP SIDE, WHAT IF SOMEBODY
SAID I WOULD NEVER HIRE THIS
PERSON ON THE OTHER SIDE, THEY
ARE PROBABLY NOT ON THE NAME OF
HIRING ANYBODY.
THERE IS ABSOLUTELY A LOGICAL
BASIS FOR WHAT SHE IS TALKING
ABOUT.
PABLO: STANFORD'S COACH SAID IT
WOULD BE NICE IF MEN AND WICK
DO WORK TOGETHER.
BO COMING UP NEXT,
DRAYMOND THROWS SOME SHADE AT
CHRIS ANDERSEN.
WE ARE GUESS MESSY.
>> NOONAN IS BROUGHT TO
What is that?
Uh mine, why?
It's just that it's...
Lavender. Yes it is, it's for
men
But I like the smell of it
Laughs
♪
We just got married.
We're all under one roof now.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
How many kids?
My two. His three.
Along with two dogs and
Jake, our new parrot.
That is quite the family.
Quite a lot of colleges
to pay for though.
A lot of colleges.
You get any financial advice?
Yeah, but I'm pretty sure
it's the same plan
they sold me before.
Well your situation's
totally changed now.
Right, right.
How 'bout a plan that works
for 5 kids,
2 dogs and Jake over here?
That would be great.
That okay with you, Jake?
Get a portfolio that works
for you now
and as your needs change
from TD Ameritrade
Investment Management.
♪ LiMu Emu & Doug ♪
Mmm, exactly!
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay
for what you need.
Nice! But uh, what's
up with your partner?
Oh! We just spend all
day telling everyone
how we customize
car insurance
because no two
people are alike, so...
LiMu gets a little
looks exactly like him.bird tht
Ya... He'll figure it out.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
Smile Dad.
gg■ ■
I take medication for
high blood pressure
and cholesterol.
But they might not be
enough to protect my heart.
Adding Bayer aspirin
can further reduce
the risk of another
heart attack.
Because my second
chance matters.
Be sure to talk
to your doctor
before you begin an
aspirin regimen.
>> HE GOT A BAD EGG.
HE A REAL BAD EGG HE GOT.
DAN: LEBRON IS A BAD EGG.
YOU WILL NOT HEAR THAT ANALYSIS
ANYWHERE.
K GOD FOR THAT BECAUSE IT
IS TERRIBLE.
>> GREETINGS, EARTH LYNX.
HIGH NOON IS BEAMED TO YOU FROM
ABOVE THE HEINEKEN RIVER DECK
AT PIER 17.
BOMANI: LAST NIGHT, WARRIORS
SMOKED THE LAKERS.
HERE IS KEVIN DURANT AND LEBRON
GETTING THEIR CASINO ON.
PABLO: THEY ARE JUST DOING THIS
TO TROLL.
THEY ARE NOT SAYING ANYTHING OF
VALUE.
BOMANI: THAT IS WHY BRIAN SHAW
IS OVER THERE LAUGHING.
THEY ARE LIKE THEY ARE GOING TO
EAT THIS UP.
WE WOULD READ THEIR LIMBS IF
THEY WEREN'T COVERING THEIRS
MOUTH.
BOMANI: I WAS TRYING.
QUOTE, TO MANY PEOPLE MAKE A
MISTAKE TRYING TO MIMIC LEBRON
WITH A TWIST, AND THAT TWIST
COMPLETELY BLEEP THE IDEA UP.
SODERLING DRAYMOND GREEN.
LET'S HEAR WHAT ELSE HE HAD TO
SAY.
>> A BLUEPRINT FOR GUYS LIKE
MYSELF AND EVERYBODY.
LIKE HE LAID THE BLUEPRINT OUT.
I THINK SO MANY PEOPLE ARE
AFRAID TO SAY THEY TRY TO
FOLLOW IT.
SO MANY PEOPLE MAKE A MISTAKE
TRYING TO LIKE MIMIC WHAT BRON
AND YOURSELF, AND MCFADDEN, AND
RICH, AND RANDY, AND ALL AVILAN
HAVE ACCOMPLISH -- AND ALL
Y'ALL HAVE ACCOMPLISHED.
PEOPLE MAKE MISTAKES TRYING TO
MIMIC IT WITH A TWIST.
OH, YEAH WE ARE GOING TO DO
THAT THAT THEY DID, AND WE ARE
GOING TO ADD THAT TWIST TO SAY
IT IS OUR IDEA.
AND THAT TWIST COMPLETELY
[BEEP]S IT UP.
IT WORKED.
BOMANI: PABLO, IF YOU WERE
KEVIN DURANT, WU THINK HE WAS
TALKING ABOUT YOU?
PABLO: I WOULDN'T BLAME KEVIN
DURANT FOR THINKING THAT, BO,
BECAUSE LEBRON JAMES HAS A SHOT
CALLED THE SHOP ON HBO.
KEVIN DURANT HAS A SHOW ON
ESPN+.
LEBRON JAMES HAS A BUNCH OF
FRIENDS THAT HE TRUSTS.
KEVIN DURANT HAS ONE RICH, WHO
IS HIS GUY.
YOU YOU GO DOWN THE LIST IN
TERMS OF HOW THEY MADE THEIR
ANNOUNCEMENTS, AND CARRIED
THEMSELVES.
IT IS SUBTWEETING.
BOMANI: YOU ARE CALLING HIM
KEVIN MCDOWELL.
HE IS BASICALLY SAYING OUR BUNS
HAVE NO MEAT.
SOMEBODY PUTS THIS UP ON THE
INTERNET, AND ALL THE THINGS
THAT LEBRON HAS DONE, THERE ARE
DIRECT SIMILARITIES BETWEEN THE
WAY KEVIN DURANT IS TRYING TO
HANDLE HIS BUSINESS AND THE WAY
THAT LEBRON JAMES IS TRYING TO
HANDLE HIS BUSINESS.
THERE IS NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.
NOW THIS WAS RECORD ADD WHILE
AGO AS WE UNDERSTAND IT.
WHAT I WANT TO KNOW IS JUST
WHAT WAS THE DRAYMOND-KEVIN
DURANT SITUATION AT THAT TIME?
HE KNEW WHAT THIS SOUNDED LIKE.
HE HAD SOMEBODY IN MIND.
PABLO: YES.
BUT DRAYMOND GREEN, IT SHOULD
BE NOTED, IF YOU MAKE A DEFENSE
OF HIM SAYING THIS INNOCENTLY,
HE IS LIVING THE WORDS HE IS
SAYING.
HE SIGNED WITH YOU CLUTCH.
I HAVE SEEN DRAYMOND GREEN,
MAVERICK CARTER AND PAUL RIVERA
HANG OUT IN A HOTEL ROOM
TOGETHER IN VEGAS.
DRAYMOND BELIEVES WHAT HE IS
SAYING, BUT IS HE ALSO SHADING
A LITTLE BIT?
NEXT QUOTE.
SYLVIA HATCHELL IS UNDER
INVESTIGATION THAT SHE MADE A
SERIOUS OF RACIAL REMARKS,
INCLUDING THE PLAYERS WOULD GET
HANGED FROM TREES IF THEIR PLAY
DIDN'T IMPROVE.
REPORTS THE WASHINGTON POST.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THESE
ALLEGATIONS.
BOMANI: THAT POST STORY IS
CRAZY.
HATCHELL HAS BEEN PUT ON
ADMINISTRATIVE LEAVE.
BOTTOM LINE, THEY ARE READING
OVER THAT CONTRACT.
THERE AIN'T NO COMING BACK FROM
WHEN THIS COMES OUT.
THEY HAD GOTTEN TO THE POINT
THAT THE PARENT GOT TOGETHER TO
PROTECT THE DAUGHTERS.
WHAT I MAKE OF THIS AS I HEAR
IT, GENO AURIEMMA, REMEMBER
WHEN WE TALKED ABOUT THAT, HE
SAID ALL THESE COACHES ARE
AFRAID TO SAY ANYTHING TO THE
PLAYERS.
THESE KIDS STUCK AROUND IN THE
MIDST OF THE MADNESS, AND
THEMSELVES COACHING ARE SCARED.
WHAT ARE THEY SCARED OF?
PABLO: WE HAVEN'T TOUCHED ON
THE MEDICAL SO SIDE OF THIS
THING.
THERE WAS A CONTROVERSY THAT
SYLVIA HATCHELL AND THE TEAM
DOCTOR, WHO IS TO BLAME MOST,
BUT WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
PLAYERS PLAYING THROUGH
SHOULDER INJURIES, CONCUSSIONS,
KNEE INJURIES, STUFF THAT GOT
EXACERBATED BECAUSE THEY WERE
BEING TO PLAY THROUGH IT.
WHAT DID THOSE PLAYERS DO?
THEY PLAYED THROUGH IT.
BECAUSE THE POWER IMBALANCE
REALLY IS IN FAVOR OF THE
PEYTON MANNINGER RATHER THAN
THE UNPAID LABOR.
THEY ARE TRYING TO SCARE OTHER
PLAYERS STRAIGHT?
NOTICE.
DEAL WITH IT ON EITHER TERMS.
BOMANI: THERE IS ANOTHER PART
WORTH NOTING HERE.
I UNDERSTAND THAT NORTH
CAROLINA WON THE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP IN 1994.
I UNDERSTAND THAT SYLVIA
HATCHELL A HALL OF FAMER.
I HAVE WATCHED ENOUGH NORTH
CAROLINA WOMEN'S BASKETBALL TO
TELL YOU SHE IS IMMINENTLY
REPLACEABLE.
PABLO: I WOULD HOPE SO.
BOMANI: WE ARE GOING TO GET
BETTER AS FAR AS PERSONNEL.
THERE IS A LOT OF TALENT OUT
THERE AND A LOT OF TALENT THAT
CAN HELP OUR FRANCHISE.
SO I WILL BE AS ACTIVE AS I
NEED TO BE.
SAID LEBRON JAMES.
DOES THIS SOIMED LIKE A SHOT AT
MAGIC JOHNSON TO YOU?
PABLO: IT SOUNDS LIKE A WAKE-UP
CALL.
THE REASON THEY GOT THE JOBS IN
THE FIRST PLACE, NOT BECAUSE
THEY ARE GOOD AT SALARY CAP
MANAGEMENT OR TEAM
CONSTRUCTION, THEY GOT THE JOB
BECAUSE ONE IS A MASTER AREA OF
DEALING WITH TALENT, AND THE
OTHER IS TO GET FREE AGENTS.
THEIR JOB IS FREE AGENT
ACQUISITION.
LEBRON IS SAYING WHY ARE YOU
GUYS MAYBE HERE?
BOMANI: TO BE HERE, THEY DID
GET ONE FREE AGENT THAT WAS A
PRETTY BIG DEAL.
THEY HAVEN'T HAD THE JOB THAT
LONG.
THIS IS NOT A SHOT AT MAGIC
BECAUSE THIS IS BASICALLY WHAT
MAGIC HIMSELF WOULD SAY.
MAGIC HAS BEEN CLEAR THAT THIS
IS THE YEAR THAT THEY HAVE TO
BRING PEOPLE IN.
THE THING THAT GETS ME ABOUT
IT, IT IS NOT JUST GOING TO BE
ABOUT YOU BEING ACTIVE IN
RECRUITING, LEBRON.
IT IS ABOUT YOU CREATING A
SITUATION THAT MAKES PEOPLE
WANT TO PLAY WITH YOU.
THERE ARE REAL QUESTIONS AS TO
WHETHER ANOTHER STAR WANTS TO
BE IN LEBRON'S ORBIT WHEN
EVERYTHING IS ABOUT LEBRON IF
YOU WIN, AND ABOUT YOU IF YOU
LOSE.
WHAT CAN THEY DO TO MITT GAME
THERE?
PABLO: WE HAVE A KEVIN DURANT,
KAWHI LEONARD, KYRIE IRVING.
WHO WILL WANT TO JOHN?
FROM THAT LIST?
MAYBE KEMBA WALKER.
PABLO: THE LAKERS SHOULD BE
ABLE TO SELL THIS, BUT WE ARE
NOT SURE ABOUT.
THAT
PABLO: NO.
BOMANI: COMING UP.
MIGHT ZION GET
CLASSIC SURRENDER COBRA.
GOOD THING I ORDERED WENDY'S.
I'VE GOT A DELICIOUS
S'AWESOME BACON CHEESEBURGER,
A BARBECUE CHEESEBURGER
AND A PEPPERCORN MUSHROOM.
DOWNLOAD OUR APP NOW
AND GET WENDY'S MADE TO CRAVE
CHEESEBURGERS DELIVERED.
I switched to Liberty Mutual,
because they let me
customize my insurance.
And as a fitness junkie,
I customize everything,
like my bike, and my calves.
Liberty Mutual customizes
d.ly pay
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
It is nice.
Yeah, but...are we
a van family?
(PTalks)
Are we a van family?
Of course you are!
Sales guy, gimme your foot.
Is it magic? No.
It's a Pacifica.
Come on in.
Allow me to do a
little self-promosh.
Check out all these features
that I got up in here.
It also comes in a hybrid.
Yo, what's up?
Van life! You know you want it.
What are you waiting for?
Let's get on the road.
But does it ever shut up?
Drive me off the lot baby,
I will sing to you
on the way home.
♪ Pacificaaaaa! ♪
Michael Jordan and Hanes
celebrate 30 years of comfort.
With exclusive Michael Jordan
trading cards.
Inside special packs of Hanes
products.
And with ten autographed by
MJ...they won't last long.
Start your collection today.
There are those who see the
challenges facing
the nation and say send me.
They fight for country.
They fight for honor.ww
They fight to win.
DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES?■■■
Find out at goarmy.com/warriors
What is that?
Uh mine, why?
It's just that it's...
Lavender. Yes it is, it's for
men
But I like the smell of it
Laughs
♪
♪ ♪
Creating the perfect night...
Just takes a little creativity.
The light beer you've been
waiting for has arrived.
Lower carbs.
Lower calories.
Higher expectations.
Corona Premier.
I can't tell you who I am
or what I witnessed,
but I can tell you Liberty
Mutual customized my
car insurance so I only
pay for what I need.
Oh no, no, no, no,
no, no, no...
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>> YUM, YUM.
HIGH NOON IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY
THE NEW WENDY'S' BIGGIE BAG.
PRICE AND PARTICIPATION MY
VARY.
BOMANI: THE JETS GOT OFF THE
CLASSIC UNIFORM LOOK.
THEY DECIDED TO GET THEMSELVES
SOME NEW UNIFORMS.
PABLO: OH, NO.
THIS IS LIKE WHAT YOU HAVE TO
DO WHEN YOU CAN'T USE THE NFL
LOGOS IN MOVIES.
BOMANI: YES.
THEY LOOK LIKE THE NEW YORK
747'S, UNIFORM PAID FOR BY
RAWLINGS.
BOMANI: THIS IS TERRIBLE.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THIS?
WHY?
BOMANI: THEY ARE THE JETS.
PABLO: TODAY'S NUMBER, $10
MILLION.
HOW MUCH NICK SAYS ONE UNNAMED
SHOE COMPANY IS IT WILLING TO
OFFER ZION WILLIAMSON PER YEAR.
ARE YOU SURPRISED AT THAT?
BOMANI: WELL, LEBRON SIGNED HIS
LEGAL IN 2003, AND IT WAS
CLOSER TO $12 MILLION A YEAR.
THE ECONOMICS OF SHOES HAVE
CHANGED, AND GUYS REALLY AREN'T
GETTING THAT BIG MONEY.
BUT THIS IS THAT DUDE.
THIS IS THE SINGLE NAME TYPE
STAR.
I EXPECT HIM TO BE THIS THAT
AREA.
PABLO: HOW MUCH CREDIT DOES
DUKE GET FOR THIS?
HE CAME INTO COLLEGE BASKETBALL
WITH LIKE A MILLION INSTAGRAM
FOLLOWERS.
TO ME, DUKE HELPED HIM SHOW HE
COULD DO THIS AGAINST PEOPLE
THAT MIGHT BE WORTHY OF
BREATHING THE SAME AIR AS HIM.
BOMANI: YOU ARE GOING TO BE IN
MORE SHOWCASE GAMES THAN
ANYWHERE ELSE AT DUKE.
IF YOU GO TO NORTH CAROLINA,
YOU WOULD BE IN THE GAMES, BUT
NOT THE SAME.
HE AT ANY TIME GET AS MUCH
VALUABLE AS DUKE GOT FOR HIM
SHOWING UP.
PABLO: IN CLOSING I WOULD LIKE
TO TAKE YOU OUT TO CLEARFIELD
HIGH SCHOOL IN UTAH, WHERE ABC
4 IS ON THE SCENE WITH THE LOT
SPORTS JOURNALISM WE
DESPERATELY NEED.
HITS WATCH.
>> STRONG ARM PITCHERS ARE
SOMETIMES SAID TO BE THROWING
GAS, BUT THIS IS DIFFERENT.
A BASEBALL COACH DOUSING THE
INFIELD WITH UNLEADED GASOLINE
AND DIESEL FUEL AND SETTING IT
ON FIRE.
THIS 8-YEAR-OLD YOUTUBE VIDEO
SHOWS THE KIND OF TECHNIQUE
THAT HEAD COACH STEVE ROSS WAS
ATTEMPTING.
>> HOLY COW.
BOMANI: LIGHT A MATCH AND RUN?
>> WOW.
PABLO: WHY?
[LAUGHTER]
>> TALK ABOUT THE HOT CORNER.
HE ONCE REPORTEDLY THREW 15-20
GALS OF FEW OVER SEVERAL AREAS.
A PARENT COMPLAINED ABOUT A
STRONG AROMA OF GASOLINE DURING
A GAME.
HE IS SUSPENDED.
THE NEXT SCHEDULED GAME HERE IS
WEDNESDAY APRIL 10TH AGAINST
NORTHRIDGE.
THAT IS IF SOMEBODY CAN HIT
CLEAN UP BEFORE THAT TIME.
>> WHOO!
PABLO: BO, HE TOOK ALL OF THE
PUNS EXCEPT THIS ONE.
I FEEL LIKE THE COACH WHO DID
THIS, HE HAS TO GET FIRED.
BOMANI: FELLAS, HELP ME OUT
HERE.
BOO!
PABLO: NO!
THAT WAS PRETTY GOOD.
BOMANI: I HAD SOMETHING PLANNED
TO SAY.
THE FIRST PARENT TO SAY DO YOU
SMELL GAS?
THE FIRST KID, WHO HAD THAT
GAS?
[LAUGHTER]
THE STORY HAS RESURFACED ABOUT
THE TIME THAT BRULES HORNSBY
BEAT ALLEN IVERSON IN
ONE-ON-ONE.
THAT'S RIGHT, IN BASKETBALL.
IT IS A LONG STORY, AND IT WAS
ABOUT IVERSON GOING TO JAIL AND
HORNSBY HELPING TO GET HIM OUT.
THEY PLAYED BALL ONE DAY, AND
HORNSBY ONE.
BUT, BUT, BUT.
HORNSBY HAS BEEN OUT HERE
TALKING ABOUT IT.
ONE THEY HAD RULES TO MAKE SURE
NOTHING HAPPENED TO THE PIANO
MAN'S HANDS.
AND THERE WERE LOTS OF
WITNESSES, WHO I PRESUME WERE
HORNS BUT'S FRIENDS.
ALLEN WAS GOING TO BEAT YOU IN
FRONT OF YOUR FRIENDS AFTER YOU
GETTING HIM OUT OF JAIL.
PABLO: THERE ARE PIANO HANDS
RULES.
NO REBOUNDS WERE ALLOWED OR
SOMETHING.
SOME CRAZY THAT MAKES THE VIDEO
OF THIS EVENT FAR LESS
IMPRESSIVE BECAUSE HORNSBY
SEEMS TO HAVE A HOME-COURT
ADVANTAGE.
BOMANI: YOU HAVE TO BE KIND
WITH THEM.
NO LIE, I ONCE SAW WITH MY EYES