SCHOOL, AND IT IS A GREAT
ELEVATION FOR HER.
SHE WAS AN ALL H- S.E.C. GUARD
AT GEORGIA, WORKED HER WAY UP
THROUGH THE GEORGIA PROGRAM,
THROUGH THE ATHLETIC DEPARTMENT
TO GET THIS JOB.
I AM NOT SAYING I AM ROOTING
FOR YOU -- FOR U.V.A., BUT
TIMELY, A BLACK WOMAN WAS ABLE
TO BREAK THROUGH IN
ADMINISTRATION.
THANK YOU, U.V.A. FOR■ING
HER A■ CHANCE.■
MIKE: "PARDON THE INTERRUPTION,"
BUT I'M MIKE WILBON.
BIG GAME TONIGHT, TONY.
WERE YOU WATCHING?
TONY: I'M TONY KORNHEISER.
MY C■/ENDS.G A BIG PARTY FOR AL■
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MIKE: I'M WATCHING TH■■
TONY: WITH WHO?
MIKE: APPARENTLY NOT WITH YOU.
TONY: THAT'S RIGHT.
MIKE: THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I, YOU KNOW --
TONY: WHEN DOES IT START?
MIKE:
TONY: OH, I THINK IT'S A 9:20
START OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I'LL GET TO HALFTIME.
MIKE: YOU AND ALL YOUR FRIENDS
WILL SNEAK OFF AND --
TONY: I GUARANTEE YOU I'LL GET
TO HALFTIME.
I'M NOT MAKING PROMISES OF THAT.
WELCOME TO "P.T.I.," BOYS AND
GIRLS.
IN TODAY'S EPISODE, TEXAS TECH
ROLLS ON, NICK SABAN WANTS
PLAYERS TO STAY, AND NOTRE DAME
LOSES A HEARTBREAKER.
WE START TODAY WITH THE■/■■
UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HEADING
TO THE FINAL GAME TONIGHT IN THE
WEIRDEST WAY.
DOUBLE DRIBB GOT A FOULN OBVIOUS
CALL ON KYLE GUY'S LAST-DITCH
THREE FROM THE LEFT CORNER, AND
GUY MADE ALL THREE FOUL SHOTS,
AND JUST LIKE■■ THAT AUBURN WAS
DONE
MIKE: HE FOULS HIM.LOOK AT THATñ
TONY: WILBON, YOU WERE THERE IN
MINNEAPOLIS.
YOU WATCHED IT.
DOES U.V.A. DESERVE TO BE
PLAYING TONIGHT?
MIKE:EL■n$b■■■b
Db A SHOOTER IZZ
jE jG= SHOULD BE■arr■■b■b■btb■b
,■bDb BECAU■=■=■=■=■=■=■=■=■=&■T
KNOW■ñn■ BECAUSE THEA IS
SO■=■=■= ■=(■■b GUTLESS IT DOESO
START A CONTROVERSY BY NOT
SHOWING THE REPLAY.
IT STARTED AONTROVERSY BY NOT
SHOWING THE REPLAY.XT MORNING I.
HE WAS SHOVED.
HE DIDN'T COME DOWN IN HIS
AIRSPACE.
KYLE GUY NAMELY NETTED THAT,
SWISH THREE FREE THROWS.
KYLE GUY WAS FOULED■ EVEN BEFORE
■z
TONY: IT'S ABSOLUTELY■z REMARKA
EY'RE HERE.
■v7v7v■v■z■vLSE.■z■z
ONE IS HOW THEY GOT TO O>z>z>z>z
AT ALL AGAINST PURDUE.
THAT PLAY,■z>z>z>z>z>z■v>z>z>z>E
GETS TO THE JUMP SHOT.
IN THIS PARTICULAR CASE, THE
CRITICAL PLAY IS KYLE GUY MAKING
THE JUMP SHOT DEEP IN THE RIGHT
CORNER THAT GETS THEM INTO A
ONE-POSSESSION SITUATION.
I JUST THINK IT'S ABSOLUTELY
REMARKABLE THAT THEY'RE THERE.
I THINK THEY DESERVE IT TOO,
BECAUSE THEY EXECUTED WHEN THEY
HAD TO.
MIKE: TWI
■zRA.
NGS THATHEM TO WIN.p
BUT IF I WAS PURDUE,■z■z■zWERE
AUBURN BE SHAKING MYEAD.
■ NIGHT IN■■IFAS
LOOKING DOWN AT CHARLES,
WHO WAS ON A SET THEY USED
HALFTIME, PREGAME AND POSTGAME.
I SAID, I FEEL BAD FOR YOU.
I FELT GREAT FOR VIRGINIA.
VIRGINIA HAS NOTHING TO
APOLOGIZE ABOUT, BUT I FEEL BAD
FOR AUBURN KIDS IN THAT
POSITION.
VIRGINIA, WERE, WAS UP 10 LATE
IN THAT GAME.
YOU THOUGHT THEY WERE GOING TO
ROLL, AND THEY DIDN'T.
THESE GAMES ARE UNBELIEVABLE.
NO UPSETS, BUT GAMES ARE
EAT.
THEY ARE.
ALL RIGHT.
VIRGINIA IS IN AFTER A SECOND
STRAIGHT MIRACLE FINISH, AND
MIGHT NEED ANOTHER ONE TO GET
PAST RELENTLESS TEXAS N
THE NCAA TITLE GAME TONIGHT.
A HANDFUL OF PEOPLE HAVE HAD
TECH WINNING THE THING FROM THE
BEGINNING.
TONY: NOT MANY.
MIKE: THE RED-HAIRED PULLED AWAD
AWAY FROM MICHIGAN STATE.
IS BASICALLY A VEGAS PICK
'EM.
TIME FOR YOU TO MAN UP.
WHO YOU GOT?
TONY: VIRGINIA HAS HAD
UNBELIEVABLE HOUDINI-LIKE■v■v G
DUKE HAD THAT SAME THING8v AGAIT
AND VIRGINIA TECH.
THEN MICHIGAN STATE KNOCKED THE■
OFF.
YOU MIGHT FAVOR TEXASXz T
■v■v■v■v■v■z■vnz
TOURNAMENT.■v■vRENCE IS VIRGINIR
THIS REASON.
NO NUMBER R LOST TO
A 16 B
BACK THE NEXT YEAR WITH
ESSENTIALLY THE SAME TEAM, THE
SAME TEAM, AND WIN THE WHOLE
THING,■v■vHAT WOULD BEC.8v8v■u
: YOU COULD WRITE BOOKS
ABOUT THAT.
MIKE: I WISH I COULD SEE ANY
SCENARIO TONIGHT, SEE TEXAS TECH
WINNING A CLOSE ONE, I COULD SEE
VIRGINIA WINNING A CLOSE ONE.
I DON'T THINK IT'S A BLOWOUT BY
THE WAY THEY PLAY, THEY'RE SO
DELIBERATE, AND THE DEFENSES ARE
SO GREAT.
TONY: I'D BE SURPRISED IF EITHER
TEAM SCORES 70.
I THINK VIRGINIA WINSOUT 70, BUó
COMFORTABLY.
THEY PLAY FREELY TONIGHT, WITH
THE BEST PLAYER IN TY JEROME■v■N
THE FLOOR.
TONY: I THINK THEY'RE FULLY
REDEEMED IF THEY WIN.
MIKE: YOU DON'T MAKE DUKE WIN
THE FINAL GAME■z■zTONY: TO B FUU
HAVE TO WIN THE WHOLE THING.
TEXAS TECH IS A RELENTLESS
DEFENSIVE TEAM.
THEY'RE A TEAM BUILT JUST FOR■v.
TO ME GRAD TRANSFERS ARE
QUARTERBACKS WHO GO SOMEWHERE
ELSE IN COLLEGE FOOTBALL,
BECAUSE IF YOU'RE SO GOOD YOU GO
TO THE NBA.
IT'S AN INTERESTING TEAM.
I COULD SEE THEM WINNING, BUT TO
ME VIRGINIA IS THE MORE COMPLETE
BETTER TEAM.
MIKE: I AGREE WITH THAT.
TEXAS TECH, JARRETT CULVER DID
NOT HAVE A GAME, I THINK HE WAS
3-12 IN THE SEMI AGAINST
MICHIGAN STATE.
THAT AIN'T GOING TO HAPPEN.
HE'LL PLAY TONIGHT.
TONY: BY THE WAY, TEXAS TECH IS
FOOTBALL SCHOOL.
FOOTBALL SCHOOLS HAVE WON MORE.
OHIO STATE A FOOTBALL SCHOOL,
FLORIDA IS A FOOTBALL SCHOOL.
WHAT VIRGINIA COULD DO HAS NEVER
BEEN DONE.
MIKE: YES.
TONY: IT'S A GRANDEUR STORY IS
WHAT I'M SAYING.
NICK SABAN IS CONCERNED AND
ANGRY THAT SEVEN OF HIS
UNDERCLASSMEN HAVE DECLARED FOR
THE NFL DRAFT.
HE WANTS TO BE SURE THAT YOU
UNDERSTAND HE'S NOT AGAINST THE
NFL.
YOU GO TO ALABAMA TO GO TO THE
NFL, BUT WHAT SABAN SAYS IS WAIT
UNTIL YOU CAN MAXIMIZE YOUR
OPPORTUNITY.
SABAN SAID, QUOTE, WE HAVE GUYS
WITH NO DRAFT GRADES,
SEVENTH-ROUND GRADES,
FIFTH-ROUND GRADES, GOING OUT IN
THE DRAFT, AND THE PLAYER LOSES.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO OUT FOR THE
DRAFT EARLY.
YOU CAN COME BACK AND PLAY,
UNQUOTE.
DO YOU BELIEVE SABAN HAS THEPLAT
HEART?
MIKE: AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED
IT'S00( PROVEN.
I DON'T BELIEVE MUCH NICK SABAN
SAYS ABOUT ANYTHING.
FIRST OF ALL, THE PROOF IS IN
THE PUDDING WHICH IS THE DR
D THE NUMBER OF PLAYERS NICK
HE HAS MORE PLAYER GOING TO THE
NFL EVERY YEAR ESSENTIALLY THE
■ OR■(!■THAN ANYBODY.
THAT INCLUDES OHIO STATE AND
SOUTHERN CAL AND PENN STATE.
SABAN PUTS MORE OF HISS
IN THE NFL.
IF YOU'RE ONE OF HIS GUYS,
YOU'RE A PARENT, GUARDIAN,
TEACHER OR ADVISOR, YOU MIGHT
WANT TO SAY DON'T TALK TO ME,
TELL ME WHAT THIS NUMBER MEANS.
NICK SABAN'S GUYS IN THE N■z■z■.
TONY:■v■v■v■v■v■v>y>y8v TERRIBLv
THE WAY HE DELIVERS A MESSAGE,
AND AS A FOOTBALL■v HE WANTS
XvIS SELFISH. DOES.
I ALSO THINK■LOT OF HIS
PUBLIC STATEMENTS ARE CORRECT.■.
THE WASHINGTON REDSKINS ON
DEFENSE ALONE HAVE EIGHT GUYS
FROM ALABAMA.
IF NICK SABAN SAYS TO YOU, SON,
I THINK YOU SHOULD WAIT ONE MORE
YEAR, I'M GOING TO LISTEN.
MIKE: IF YOU DON'T, YOU
SHOULDN'T BE EARTH ANGRY AT HIM.
TONY: I DON'T THINK MANY[z■v■v D
ONE MORE S■P YOU.
MIKE:$ WE'VE■ú OUR■ARE OF PERSO(
((((( TO GIVE THE■■■■■■■■■■
COACHED BYG NICK SABAN AN HIS
STAFF.
TONY: BECAUSE HE WINS ALL THE
TIME.
MIKE: HOW CAN YOU MAKE THE CASE
WITH A STRAIGHT FACE THAT NICK
SABAN DOESN'T CARE?
TONY: AGAIN, EVEN IF I DON'T
LIKE THE MESSENGER, THE MESSAGE
IS ACCURATE.
MIKE: HARD NOT TO LI
TONY.
STORMY DANIELS' LAWYER, SOME
DUDE NAMED MICHAEL AVENATTI
ARRESTED LAST MONTH FOR TRYING
TO EXTORT NIKE TWEETED OVER THE
WEEKENDED THAT NIKE PAID ZION
WILLIAMSON'S MOM■=■■■■■1■
CONSULTING FEES AS P OF A■
BRIBE■■ ZION TO DUKE.
THE SCHOOL WILL INVESTIGATE.
BIG DEAL,hv■v■p■v4y LITTLE DEALL
AT ALL?
TONY: BILL PA■v■vyvyvyvyzyv■zyvT
PREJUDICE YOURSELF.
■v■p■v■v■v BEEN CALLED A LOW RE.
THAT MAY■z B■v■v■v■v■v■zXv MAY .
I'M PROBABLY BEING NAIVE, BUT I
LOOK AT ZION■v WILLIAMSON,■=■=■S
KID IS SO GOOD, HE'LL GET ALL
THE MONEY INORLD'S
■v HIM.
MAYBE SOMEBODY TOOK MONEY.■v■v■v
ING, I4yE RECALL,■v■z
THINnz■z■■■■
I'M NOT GOING BIG DEAL, LITTLE
DEGREE, NO DEAL, BUT I WILL SAY
THAT IF RULES ARE BROKEN -- IF
YOU THINK THE RULES STINK,
CHANGE THE RULES.
KANSAS ISN'T TOO BIG, ARIZONA
ISN'T TOO BIG, AUBURN■
BIG THAT THEY DON'T HAVE TO OBEY
MIKE: BIG D■■ LITTLT
DEAL.
WE'VE BEEN■ INUNDATED WITH THESE
STORIES.
S ARE VERY LEGITND A HALF.
ABOUT FAMOUS PEOPLE BRIBING
SCHOOLS --
TONY: ALLEGEDLY THEY'LL BE
GUILTY.
MIKE: THIS LESS THAN NO DEAL IN
THIS CONTEXT, TONY.
I DON'T CARE.
TONY: WELL, YOU DON'T CARE.
MIKE: PEOPLE DON'T CARE.
I JUST LEFT MINNEAPOLIS.
NEARLY A HUNDRED THOUSAND PEOPLE
32 WATCH BASKETBALL.
MOST OF THEM THOUGHT THEY WERE
GOING TO WATCH
TO
YOU RE.
MIKE: TONY,■■■ NOBODY I KNOW.I !
I K DAN ABOUT
THIS.
TONY: MIKE, THESE ARE NOT LAWS.
THESE ARE NCAA RULES.
THESE ARE NOT■■■■ L?OT THAT
SISTANT COACHES ARE GOING TO
JAIL FOR BRIBERY.
SO SOMEBODY OUT THERE CARES.
MY POINT IS SIMPLY THIS.ó
IF YOU HAVE THE RULE, AND THEY
DON'T ENFORCE THE R WHAT DO
WE DO IT?
SHOE COMPANIES HAVE BEEN
SLIPPING MONEY TO PEOPLE FOR THE
LAST 40 YEARS.
TONY: YES, I DO BELIEVE THAT.
WE TURN NOW TO THE WOMEN'S FINAL
LAST NIGHT.
BAYLOR BEAT NOTRE DAME IN WHAT
BECAME A CLOSE GAME, DENYING
NOTRE DAME THE CHANCE TO REPEAT
AS NATIONAL CHAMPIONS.
NOTRE DAME WAS DOWN TWO POINTS
WITH 1.9 SECONDS TO PLAY WHEN
ARIKE■OWALE STEPPED TO THE
LINE, AND MADE THREE SHOTS.
SHE WAS 33-36 FROM THE
THIS TOURNAMENT.
SHE MISSED THE FIRST.
GAME OVER.
HOW DID YOU FEEL WHEN SHE
MISSED?
MIKE: I WOULD HAVE GIVEN HER A
STANDING OVATION.
SHE WON HER A SCHOOL A NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP A YEAR AGO.
SHE'S PLAYED VALIANTLY ALL T
xSHE'S@@ GETTING A
BRIB■ SHOE COMPANY, BUT
PLAYED AS■■AYING COLLEGEñn BASK.
STANDING OVATION, TONY.A
TONY: SO I FELT REALLY BAD FOR
HER, BECAUSEHE NIGHT BEFORE
KYLE■ GUY MADE THOSEHREE SAND H.
I WILL SAY I
AME.
BAYLORON THAT GAME.
NOTRE DAME DIDN'T LOSE THAT
GAME.
BAYLOR WAS UP 17, AND NOTRE DAME
CAME ROARING BACK AND TOOK THE
LEAD, AND BAYLOR HAD CRITICAL
BUCKETS.
BAYLOR DID THE RIGHT.
BAYLOR DID NOT FOLD UP.
I'M LOOKING AT KIM MULKEY, WHO
IS THE RARE PERSON WHO NOT ONLY
WON NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP AS
PLAYER.
GOOD FOR THEM.
■O WAY, THEIR BEST PLAYER,
COUT  MOST OF
THE SECOND HALF.
MIKE: SO BAYLOR HAS NOW INSERTED
DAME.TCONN■!
THINK THOSE THREE, AND
OTHER SCHOOLS LIKE SOUTH
CAROLINA, STANFORD, THEY'VE
BUBBLED UP, BUT I THINK THESE
THREE ARE AT THE TOP OF THE
WOMEN'S BASKETBALL PYRAMID.
TONY: ILDN'T PUT NOTRE DAME
AHEAD OF BAYLOR.
MIKE: I SAID BAYLOR IS WITH
UCONN, AND NOTRES S
BELOW.
THEY W■ SORRY, TELLWON THE
+■■T YEAR WITH THE
TONY: KNOCKED OUT UCONN.
BIG DEAL.
LET'S TAKE A BREAK.
A REPLAY OF THE END OF LAST
NIGHT'S LOSS?
MIKE: AND SHOULD RICK BARNES
CONSIDER STRONGLY LEAVING
TENNESSEE FOR CAKE.
UCLA?TONY: YOU THINK VIRGINIA WS
COMFORTABLY TONIGHT?
♪ ♪
Plants capture CO2.
What if other kinds ó■■■too?■ 8
If these industrial plants had
techno■=■=■;■;■;ñ;ç8j
that captured carbon like trees
we could help lower emissions.
Carbon Capture is important
technology -
and experts agree.
That's why we're working on ways
to improve it.
So plants...
can be a little more...
like plants.
♪ ♪
Rated M for mature.
One bullet left...
...who's it for?
The strong?
The weak?
Or the hopeless?
This world will come for
you, and it will never stop.
One bullet left...
...who's it for?
I was tired
of having my calls dropped,
and then I'd heard that I could
get Apple Music
if I switched over
and I said, "BOOM!"
(VO)
The best network is even better
with Apple Music
on us.
Plus save big when you switch.
Only on Verizon.
New lower price.
Wow. That's a lot
of asparagus.
Yeah, you said get
a bunch of asparagus.
Oh, you...
bunch.
I... thought you kinda...
♪ LiMu Emu & Doug ♪
bunch.
Mmm, exactly!
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay
for what you need.
Nice! But uh, what's
up with your partner?
Oh! We just spend all
day telling everyone
how we customize
car insurance
because no two
people are alike, so...
LiMu gets a little
looks exactly like him.■■■■otht
Ya... He'll figure it out.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroand .
All I had to dve my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.■■ñ■■■■
What would she do without me?
TONY: IT'S MAIL TIME.
HIGH-LEVEL ANSWERS TO LOW-LEVEL
QUESTIONS.
MIKE: MAN, YOU INSULTING ME.
TONY: SHOULD THE OFFICIATING
MISTAKE LIKE THE ONE IN THE
HEAT-RAPTORS LEADf■ TO A REPLAYG
OF THE FINAL SECONDS OF
REGULATION?
MIKE: YEAH.
I KNOW THE FINAL 10 SECONDS WERE
BOTCHED.
THE BALL HASN'T BEEN INBOUNDED.
MY PROBLEM IS TORONTO HAS GONEHR
COUNTRY, I HAVEN'T LOOKED
CLOSEL THEIR SCHEDULE, YOU
CAN'T REPLAY THIS.
IF ANOTHER TEAM INVOLVED WAS
ORLANDO, DETROIT, MIAMI,
CHARLOTTE, I MEAN A TEAM LOOKING
FOR A SPOT, I WOULD SAY MAYBE
YOU HAVE TO REPLAY IT.
AS IS, I WOULD NOT REPLAY THIS.
WOULD YOU?
TOITE, I MIGHT HAVE
REPLAYED IT.
MIKE: NO.
BUT THEY'RE NOT ON SITE ANYMORE.
TONY: YOU GOT THE BALL WITHIN 10
SECONDS.
YOU HAD TIME TO PUT UP A PLAY, A
GOOD SHOT, AND THEN YOU WENT TO
OVERTIME.
SO YOU HADIN■zE.
SPARE ME THE SYMPATHY FOR MIAMI
IN■z■z THIS PARTICULAR CASE, BEE
THAT GAME.OTS OF TIME TO
MIKE: A LOT OF US WANT TO SEE
NE WADE IN THES.
TONY: STOP LOSING FOUR IN A ROW.
MIKE: BOTTOM OF THE EAST NOT
LOOKING ALL THAT POWERFUL RIGHT
NOW.
TONY: NO.
MIKE: WOULD UCLA BE AN UPGRADE
■■ TENNESSEE FOR COACH RICK
BARNES?
TONY: SO I FEEL UCLA IS A GIANT
UPGRADE OVER TENNESSEE.
BUT I'M OLD.
I REMEMBER JOHN WOODEN AND UCLA.
MIKE: URN ERNIE AND BERNIE?
TONY: I REMEMBER ERNIE AND
BERNIE, BUT THEY DIDN'T WIN IT.
IF YOU LOOK AT RICK BARNES, RICK
BARNES HAS COACHED IN
PROVIDENCE, COACHED IN CLEMSON,
SOUTHA, KNOXVILLE,
TENNESSEE.
MIKE: WASHINGTON, D.C.
TONY: BRIEFLY, I THINK FOR ONE
YEAR AT GEORGE MASON.
AND AUSTIN, TEXAS.
HE HASN'T BEEN AN L.A. GUY.
HE MAY NOT WANT TO GO TO L.A.
THE S.E.C. RIGHT NOW, AUBURN,
TENNESSEE, L.S.U., KENTUCKY, FAR
BETTER THAN THE PAC-12.
FAR BETTER     AT'S TRUE.
I'LL SAY T TONY, THIS WOULD
BE A UPGRADE, A"G ONE,
BECAUSE EVERY VOTE AT TENNESSEE
WILL TILT TOWARD FOOTBALL.
THAT'S GOING TON.
AND■
ALREADY BEEN KNOWS THE DEAL.
NOT THE CASE AT UCLA.
TO
MIKE: IF HE WINS
EVERYWHERE RICK BARNES HAS GONE,
HE'S BEEN■ GOOD.
TONY: IT SHOULD BE IRRESISTIBLE
TO HIM.
DOES YASIEL PUIG DESERVE A
■p■■■ú■ú
MIKE: NO.
HE DESERVES RIDICULE.
■DY PITCHERS OFF A HOME
RUN.
I WOULD HAVE THROWN SOMETHING AT
HIM WHILE HE WAS STANDING THERE.
THIS THING BEHIND THE PLATE, THE
SCRAP AFTER THEY THROW BEHIND
HIM IN HIS NEXT AT-BAT, IT
LASTED FOR NEARLY 20 MINUTES,
AND IT WAS NOTHING.
IT WAS NOTHING.
THEY SHOULD HAVE GONE OUT THERET
NO PUNCHES WERE THROWN.
THEY DAN■ 20 MINUTES.
RIDICULE.
TONY: I THINK HE■= DOES E A
SUSPENSION.
WAS BEING HELD ■z■
PITTSBURGH PLAYER, JOEY VOTTO,
NCINNATI, AND ESCAPED AND
ATTEMPTED TO ATTACK THE
ENTIRE --
MIKE: DID HEK ANYBODY?
TONY: YASIEL PUIG WANTED TO SHOW
HIS TEAMS HE WAS A STANDUP GUY.
HE)z PROLONGED THIS■■■■ STUPIDI.
HE PROLONGED IT.
MIKE: HE WASN'T ACTUALLY GOING
TO ATTACK ANYBODY.
TONY: LET'S TAKE ONE LAST BREAK.
STILL TO COME, JOSH ROSEN, YOUR
BOY, HAS A RESPONSE FOR THOSE
WHO THOUGHT HE MIGHT NOT SHOW UP
FOR O.T.A.'S.
MIKE: WE'RE TALKING AGAIN ABOUT
O.T.A.'S ON THIS SHOW?
TONY: YEAH.
MIKE: IS MIKING TROUT GETTING
BETTER?
DOES ANYBODY KNOW WHO HE IS
OUTSIDE OF CALIFORNIA?
TONY: HE'S EARNING THE MONEY
THEY'RE GIVING HIM.
MIKE: HE ALWAYS EARNS IT.
TONY: YOU CAN'T GIVE HIM TOO
MUCH
These days, travel can feel
like you're in a battle scene.
we've rewritten the script  ,
With — spoiler alert —
no suspense, no surprises
and definitely no shocks.
When it comes to drama,
let's leave that
to the Avengers.
Hertz.
We're here to get you there.
Marvel Studios
Avengers: Endgame
♪♪
in theaters April 26th.
With Free Cancellations...
Bookers book now
and ask their boss later.
This is Ode
to State Farm
awards in a row
( ♪♪ )
In B minor.
Woman:
Great stuff.
■■ ■ ■ ■
( ♪♪ )
Oh, wow. You two are going to
have such a great trip.
Thanks to you, we will.
This is why Voya helps reach
today's goals...
...all while helping you to and
through retirement.
Can you help with these?
We're more of the plan, invest
and protect kind of help...
Voya. Helping you to
and through retirement.
♪  ♪
Turn up your swagger
game with One A Day Gummies.
One serving...
...once a day...
.. ...and one healthy you.port
6 vital functions...
That's The Power of One A Day.
Neprice.
Wow. That's a lot
of asparagus.
Yeah, you said get
a bunch of asparagus.
Oh, you...
A bunch.
I... thought you kinda...
I was tired
of having my calls dropped,
and then I'd heard that I could
get Apple Music
if I switched over
and I said, "BOOM!"
(VO)
The best network is even better
with Apple Music
on us.
Plus save big when you switch.
Only on Verizon.
That they and their families
would get the benefits
and support they earned.
We fight for all veterans so
that promise is kept.
DAV.
For help, visit DAV.org.
>> OH, NO.
THIS IS WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO WHEN
YOU CAN'T USE THE NFL LOGOS IN
MOVIES.
>> YES.
THEY LOOK LIKE THE NEW YORK 747.
TONY: HAPPY TIMES, PEOPLE.
HA■ BIRTHDAY FEEL
HERNANDEZ.
ONCE A CY YOUNG WINNER IN THE
ACKNOWLEDGED ACE OF THE SEATTLE
MARINERS STAFF, HERNANDEZ IS
COMING OFF AN 8-14 SEASON WITH A
STUNNING 5.55 E.R.A.
HERNANDEZ WILL MAKE HIS SECOND
START OF THE SEASON TONIGHT FOR
SEATTLE, WHICH HAS THE BEST
RECORD IN BASEBALL AT 9-2.
THIS YEAR FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE 2008 HERNANDEZ DID NOT
START OPENING DAY.
MIKE: IS THAT 9-2 MARK, TONY, IS
ALSO THE BEST START IN FRANCHI■E
SEATTLEwñ■■■w A GREAT SEASON A
WHILE AG
TONY: WITH LOU PINIELLA.
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY, HANK AARON.
ON THI DAY 45 YEARS AGO, YOU
BROKE BABE RUTH'S CAREER HOME
RUN RECORD BY HITTING YOUR 715TH
IN ATLANTA'S HOME OPENER.
YOU HIT IT OFF AL DOWNING THEN
WITH THE DODGERS.
AS YOU CAN SEE IN THE VIDEO, TWO
KIDS GOT ON THE FIELD AND JOINED
AARON ROUNDING THIRD BASE.
WAITING FOR HIM AT HOME PLATE
WAS A CRAIG SAGER.
DESPITE HOW MANY HOME RUNS BARRY
BONDS■■■■■■■■■■■■■ PEOPLE, LIKE
MIKE AND I, CONSIDER AARON THE
HOME RUN KING.
MIKE: HE ISHE HOME RUN KING.
TONY: HAPPY TRAILS TO THE WNBA
FOR SABRINA IONESCUINB■
D OREGON TO THE FINAL FOUREAR
THIS YEAR FOR THE FIRST TIME
EIG.
MIKE: SHE CAN CHANGE THE GAME,
TONY.
WHAT ABOUT OFFERED SOMETHING IN
EUROPE, WHERE WOMEN MAKE MORE
MONEY PLAYING PROFESSIONAL
BASKETBALL THAN THE UNITED
STATES.
TONY: WOULDN'T SHE BE THE NUMBER
ONE PICK NEXT YEAR AS WELL?
■t■■■c■■■■qqqqqqTHINK■■■■■ñ■t■■N
JOSH ROSEN, WASST
I'M SURE YOU'RE■■■.'S.
MIKE: DON'T GIVE PEOPLE CREDITp.
HE'S THEERBACK.
PHIL HOUSLEY FIRED.
IS THAT JUSTIFIED?
TONY: DOESN'T MAKE THE PLAYOFFS.
THE LAST WEEK, ABOUT 10 HOCKEYhz
hz■z■z■z■z■z■v■z■z■z■z■z BOYyzy.
ERICUSSELMAN LEAVING N
IS THAT■ AN UP■u■u
MIKE: KNOW.
I WANT TO SAY NO
TONY:■■■■■■■■■■■■■■ REALLY?
MIKE: HE THE TOURNAMEN
TONY: ARKANS WON THE
NATIONAL TITLE.
MIKE: MIKE TROUT HAD FIVE HOME
RUNS IN A FOUR-GAME SERIES.
IS THIS HIS BEST SEASON?
ONLY IN THREE PLAYOFF GAMES.yzyv
AS GREAT AS HE IS, THEY DON'T
WIN.
THE ■v■v■v■v DEPRIVED OF
SEEING THIS GUY.8p8p8p8v■v8p8p■O
AT-BATS AWAY OF TYING THE RECORD
FOR CONSECUTIVE HITLESS AT-BATS.
WHAT HAPPENS TONIGHT?MIKE: TWO .
TWO HITS.
MAYBE IN BALTI WHERE FANS