LAST WORD.
MY CAREER CALLING IT OUT.
I GET TO DO IT ON MY OWN.
OMITTED IT BECAUSE OF NEWS OF
THE DAY AND TIME.
NO CONSEQUENCE.
THINK PROGRESS IS COVERED.
STARTED THE CONVERSATION THAT WE
I'M SORRY..
I APOLOGIZE.
IT'S A CONVERSATION WE NEED TO
BE HAVING, ABOUT AN OPPORTUNITY
GAP AND PAY GAP AND CONVERSATION
THAT
MIKE: "PARDON THE INTERRUPTION,"
BUT I'M MIKE WILBON.
TONY, A STORE OWNER HAS VIDEO OF
A SHOPLIFTER STUFFING A CHAIN
SAW DOWN HIS PANTS.
ARE YOU BUYING THAT?
TONY: I'M TONY KORNHEISER.
HERE'S WHAT YOU DON'T WANT TO
AR, A CHAIN SAW.
I SAW HIM STUFF THE CHAIN SAW
DOWN THE FRONT OF --
MIKE: WHERE DID YOU SEE IT?
TONY: ON "THE TODAY SHOW" DURIN.
MIKE: I'M NOT BUYING IT.
HOW TALL IS IT?
TONY: DO YOU THINK ALL CHAIN
SAWS ARE 8 FEET TALL?
MIKE: YES.
TONY: NO.
IT WAS A BABY CHAIN SAW.
WELCOME TO "P.T.I.," BOYS AND
GIRLS.
IT'S FRIDAY.
WE'RE BOTH HERE.
WHO HAD THE OVERUNDER ON THAT?
IN TODAY'S EPISODE, GIANNIS,
YOUR CUBS ARE HORRIBLE, AND
PATRICK MAHOMES IN A THROWING
CONTEST.
WE BEGIN WITH THE FINAL
RROW IN MINNEAPOLIS
AUBUIGANTE, TE■
TECH AND VIRGINIA REMAIN■;x=
WILL BE THERE.
MIKE: THAT'S RIGHT.
TONY: MICHIGAN STATE IS FROM
YOUR CONFEHE BIG TEN,
AND YOUR WIFE WEDNESDAY TO
VIRGINIA AS AN UNDERGRAD.
ARE■66
MY DEERE FRI
LES BARKLEY, AND I K
D BE TOO, BUT THEY'RE
MISSING THEIR BEST PLAYER, HARD
TO GET OVER THAT.■■SOME COACHESG
DEAN SMITH AMONG THEM, THAT FOR
THE NEXT GAME, THE FIRST GAME
WITHOUT ON■; YOUR BEST
THROUGH THE FIRST GAMTTOGETHER,
HIM.
AUBURN DID T
NOW YOU'RE ASKING THEM TO GO
OTHER GAME, I THINK
THNG TO BECULT.
I THINK MICHIGAN STATE IS THE
BEST TEAM OF THE FOUR.
TONY: I AGREE WITH THAT.
SHAME ON THE NCAA FOR PUTTING
MICHIGAN STATE AND DUKE IN THE
SAME --
MIKE: STOÃNING ABOUT DUKE.
, NO, NO.
I WANT TO TELL YOU SOMETHING,
WHEN ZION WILLIAMSON WENT OUT,
HE SUCKED THE A
TOURNAMENT.
FOUR TEAMS WITHOUT ANY STARS.
TWO FOOTBALL SCHOOLS.
VIRGINIA HAS NO NATIONAL
FOLLOWING IN PARTICULAR, AND
MICHIGAN STATE THERE FOR A LONG
TIME.
THIS IS A TELEVISION SHOW.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MANY PEOPLE ARE
GOING TO GO TO THEIR TELEVISION
SETS TO SEE THE FIRST TWO GAMES.
MIKE: MILLIONS, MILLIONS.
TONY: NOT AS MANY MILLIONS AS
THEY EXPECT.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE MICHIGAN STATE
AND VIRGIN■■■■■■USED TO■■■■■■■■I
HAVINGf HIM., LEBRON JAMES, NOT
THEY NEVER HAD HIM. WAS A TRANST
OF HIGH SCHOOL HAD, EVEN THAN
MORE HAD SO THAN ZION, AND THE
TOURNAMENT DID FINE.
TONY: COLLEGE HAD ZION, AND NOW
THEY DON'T HAVE HIM.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE APPEALGgG.
ST.
YOUR BRACKET?
TONY: YOU HAD THE RIGHT CALcgcg.
MIKE: I LOVE DUKE, WISH THEY
WERE■■ /■■■■D PHILLY LAST NIGHTD
■■■E
S RETHINK■■■ 8VERY
HIS 45, 13 AND 6■■■■■■■> ASSIST■
BLOCKS, IN 35 MINUTES, TOOK OUT
THE SIXers, WRAPPED UP THE TO■■D
SUGGESTED THAT VOTERS TAKE
ANOTHER LONG HARD LOOK AT THEIR
M.V.P. BALLOTS.
TONY, ARE YOUR PLAYOFF
EXPECTATIONS OF HIM AND THE
BUCKS CHANGING?
AND DO YOU THINK MILWAUKEE COULD
LEGITIMATELY CHALLENGE THE DUBS?
TONY: THAT'S WAY DOWN THE ROAD.
I'M NOT EVEN GOING TO DEAL WITH
THAT NOW.
THE PLAYOFFS LAST FOR THREE
MONTHS.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT
ANTETOKOUNMPO FOR A SECOND.
I MEAN, HE'S NOT LEBRON.
HE'S NOT STEPH CURRY.
HE'S NOT KEVIN DURANT.
WHEN YOU LUMP THE YOUNG BIG MEN
TOGETHER, WHEN YOU HAVE EMBIID
AND KARL-ANTHONY DOWNS AND
ANTHONY DAVIS AND THIS KID, THIS
THE KID I WANT RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE I THINK HE'S MORE
VERSATILE.
IN THREE GAMES HEAD-TO-HEAD WITH
EMBIID, AND EMBIID HAD GREAT
NUMBERS, ANTETOKOUNMPO HAD GREAT
NUMBERS.
IN THOSE THREE GAMES AGAINST THE
GUY YOU'VE GOT TO BEAT IN YOUR
CONFERENCE, HE WENT FOR 42
POINTS, ALMOST 16 REBOUNDS, AND
8 ASSISTS.
EVERYBODY SAYS THAT THE CENTER
POSIE BIG MAN POSITION,
IS■■■■■>■■■■/■/>■.■>■.■■■.■■■■■T
THIS POINT.
PART B'■■■■■.■.■ KNOW,■■■■■■■■■>
EMBIID GOT BEAT.
ANTETOKOUNMPO IS MAKING■í■7■7■■■
ANTETOKOUNMPO ISN'T GREAT EVERY
NIGHT -- AND MICHAEL BROGDON IS
NOT OUT THERE --
TONY: I THOUGHT IT WAS KHRIS
MIDDLETON.
HE'S AN ALL-STAR.
MIKE: THEY ARE CHANGING MY
EXPECTATIONS A LITTLE BIT.
I'M NOT READY TO LOOK AT GOLDEN
STATE AND THEM EITHER, BUT CAN
THEY BEAT BACK THE CELTICS, THE
SIXERS, AND ULTIMATELY TORONTO?
TONY: I THINK THE CELTICS ARE A
DIFFICULT OUT FOR EVERYBODY.
MIKE: YEAH, BUT YOU'RE STARTING
TO MOVE A LITTLE BIT.
TONY: THEY'RE IMPRESSIVE.
THEY'RE IMPRESSIVE.
HERE'S WHAT'S NOT IMPRESSIVE,
AND HERE WE GO, MR. CUB.
YOUR BASEBALL TEAM LOST AGAIN
LAST NIGHT.
YOUR BULLPEN IMPLODED AGAIN LAST
NIGHT.
THREE RELIEVERS GAVE UP SIX RUNS
IN FOUR -- COUNT THEM -- FOUR
INNINGS.
THE COLLECTIVE BULLPEN E.R.A. IS
8.86.
MIKE: UP FROM 8.83.
TONY: THEY HAVE LOST 19 MEN IN
20 1/3 INNINGS.
CAN JOE MADDON'S JOB BE ON THE
LINE?
LOST EVERYTHING SINCE.■>■>■>■>■■
WILL.
TONY: THEY'VE BEEN ON THE ROAD
THE WHOLE TIME.
MIKE: YEAH, THEY HAVE.
THE BUT, TONY, PEOPLE LOOK AT
THIS, AND THEY THINK THAT THE
EXECUTIVES LOOK AT MADDON AND
SAY ALL THIS STUFF IS NICE AND
CUTE AND FURY WHEN IT WORKED.
NOW IT'S NOT WORKING.G■G■G■GvG■■
CHICAGOG■GvG■G■G■GvG■GvG■G■ERE
GvGvGvGv'■'■'■G>'■■■.■.■■.■.■.■■
TO THE FINALS TWO OR THREE OTHER
TIMES, HE'S GONE, FIRED.
THIS IS NOT UNPRECEDENTED.
TONY: I'LL DEAL WITH THAT IN A
SECOND.
FIRST THE BREWERS ARE 6-1 AT THE
MOMENT.
A GUYq=■8q=q=LD BE FIRED,
LET ALONE WITHIN THREE SEASONS.
HERE'S A QUOTE FROM THEO
EPSTEIN, WHO I KNOW YOU THINK IS
A GREAT EXECUTIVE.
FROM DECEMBER, QUOTE, THIS YEAR
IS A RECKONING.
I FEEL WE UNDERPERFORMED.
JUDGE US ON HOW WE PLAY NEXT
YEAR.
THIS IS NEXT YEAR.
MIKE: WHAT DOES THAT SAY TO YOU?
TONY: I HAD RICHIE JUSTICE ON
THE PODCAST AND HE BELIEVES JOE
MADDON IS ON A HOT SEAT, THAT
THERE WAS A CULT OF PERSONALITY
THAT GREW UP AROUND JOE MADDON,
AND THAT HE DIDN'T GIVE TIME TO
BASEBALL.
OF THE BELL STINKS.
MIKE: NOW THE BULLPEN CAN'T GET
OUT YOU AND ME.
TONY: ONLY ONE BULLPEN WORSE IN
THEG■■■G■G■G■G■G■E,G■G■G■G■G■G■-
MIKE: THE ONLY REASON WE EVER
TALK ABOUT THE ORIOLES IN RECENT
YEARS IS TO MAKE FUN OF THEM,
WHICH MICE ME TO CHRIS■
THE ONE-TIME ALL-STAR STILL
BEING PAID LIKE A SLUGGER.
OF THE THEREAR■;■;■;■;
THAT'S LED TO HIM GOING■;■;■;■■7
THIS SEASON, AREh■J■h■h■a■■■■■■G
BACK TO LAST SEASON.
THE MANAGER SAYS HE'LL KEEP HIM
IN THE LINEUP WHEN HE CAN.
OF IS THE ROOKIE MANAGER TO
STANDBY HIS SLUGGER?
TONY: NO ONE'S HEARD OF THIS
MANAGER.
WE'VE BEEN TO A LOT OF GAMES IN
BALTIMORE.
THEY'RE NOT A HYPOCRITICAL
CROWD.
THIS MAY BE OVER.
FOR ALL THE MONEY HE--
MIKE: $23 MILLION A YEAR FOR THE
NEXT FOUR YEARS, INCLUDING THIS
ONE.
TONY: YOU HAVE TO EAT SOME OF
THAT, MOST OF THAT, BUT IT
BECOMES AFTER A WHILE A MENTAL
HEALTH ISSUE.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET THIS GUY OUT
OF THERE.
WHEN YOU'RE CHEERING PITCH
HITTERS -- THIS IS A BAD
CIRCUMSTANCE.
CHRIS DAVIS IN 2013 HIT 53
HOMERS, 138 R.B.I.'S.
MI MAYBE■ ABOUT LAUNCH■■■ AND7/■
ANGLE.
THE CUBS CHANGED A HITTING A
PITCHING COACH AND --
TONY: CHANGED EVERYBODY.
MIKE: NOW HE'S FORGOT HOW TO
HIT?
TONY: I DON'T KNOW IF HE FORGOT
HOW TO HIT.
I SAY YOU LOOK AT SOMETHING LIKE
THAT, IN A CITY LIKE BALTIMORE,
WHICH IS NOT PHILADELPHIA, AND
IT MAY BE BEST FOR CHRIS DAVIS
TO FIND ANOTHER PLACE TO PLAY.
MIKE: YEAH.
THAT'S A LOT OF MONEY TO EAT.
TONY: GOT TO EAT MOST OF IT.
THERE'S A TANTALIZING POSSIBLY
IN THE WIND THAT YOUNG GUNS
PATRICK MAHOMES AND JOSH ALLEN
MAY HAVE A THROWING CONTEST TO
TOSEE WHO HAS THE LONGER ARM.
MAHOMES SAID NO ONE THAT I'VE
THANN HAS THROWN A BALL FARTHER■
I'VE NEVER SEEN JOSH IN PERSON,
BUT MAYBE NEXT OFF-SEASON WE CAN
SET SOMETHING UP.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE 85 YARDS TO
WIN.
WILBON, IS THIS SOMETHING YOU'D?
I COVERED IN FOOTBALL WHEN
REPORTERS COO PRACTICE.
YOU DID TOO■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■;
PRACTICE O■■■■■ AND THIS?7■■?7■■
BELIEVE, A TIGHT END AND THE
IT WAS3>W■L■■■L■L■L■?;■;L■L■■■■.
I DON'T THINK IT MEANS ANYTHING.
BUT I LIKE THE FACT THAT MAHOMES
IS STILL WILLING TO DO THIS KIND
OF THING.
TONY: I ASSUME THE BEST ARM
YOU'VE EVER SEEN IS JOHN ELWAY.
MIKE: YES.
TONY: I WOULD SAY JEFF GEORGE.
I USED TO WATCH■X■X■X■
HE WAS TOL WARMUPS WHAT
STEPH CURRY IS TO BASKETBALL
NOW.
THAT DIDN'T MAKE HIM A GREAT
QUARTERBACK --
MIKE: AS MUCH AS YOU KNOW
THINK JOHN ELWAY IS GREAT, JEFF
GEORGE WOULD DO THINGS THAT --
TONY: A ANALOGY, RORY MCILROY
CAN DRIVE THE BALL 340 YARDS,
BUT THE GUY IN THE LONG DRIVE
CONTEST CAN DRIVE IT 400 YARDS,
BUT THEG■G■.■.■■■G/.■■■.■.■■■■■■
LONGER.
MIKE: MAHOMES CAN PLAY AND A GUY
WITH A LONG DRIVE.
I THINK NO ONE PROBABLY IN THE
LEAGUE CAN THROW IT AS FAR AS
PATRICK MAHOMES.
TONY: YOU CAN FIND A GUY ON A
STREET CORNER WHO CAN THROW IT A
HUNDRED.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S A
QUARTERBACK, BUT HE CAN THROW IT
A HUNDRED.
MIKE: HOW FAR COULD GRONK THROW
IT?
TONY: HE WOULD EAT THE FOOTBALL.
LET'S TAKEq A BREAK.
BUT COMING UP ON THE EVE OF THE
FINAL FOUR IS ANYONE SURPRISEDAL
COACHING AT AUBURN?
MIKE: AND REGGIE MILLER SAYS
HE'S SEEN THE BEST PRACTICE HE'S
EVER SEEN.
I switched to Verizon because
I was tired
of having my calls dropped.
I had friends that were
next to me
and they weren't having
these issues and they said
like, "You need to switch!"
And then I'd heard
that I could get Apple Music
if I switched over
and I said, "BOOM!"
Music is very important to me.
I come from
the techno era,
but I'm hip-hop at heart.
(VO)
The best network is even better
with more music on us.
Get Apple Music
included with Unlimited.
Plus save big when you switch.
Only on Verizon.
♪ Ooooh I■overing,
I'm discovering Ooooh ♪
■
■■666
Bring color to life with
the very best paint,
only at your
Sherwin-Williams store.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
AAll I had to do was give my,
ahuman “the look”.a.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.■ññññ■ñ
What would she do without me?
Emerge Restored,
Replenished,
Fortified.
Emerge everyday with Emergen-C.
Packed with B vitamins,
Electrolytes, Antioxidants,
Plus more vitamin C than
10 oranges.
Why not feel this good
every day?
Emerge and See.
$10 pres■■í■■ our si sirloin st.
Chili's 3 for $10 presenour e
sirloin steak.
Aged to perfection
and served withged to n
a starter and drink
for just $10.
Dinner with mom, dad,
grandma and her friend Randy,
who seems to be a little more
than a friend.
Together We Chili's.
I'm head coach Jay Wright
E■■1■1■1■#■■■■■@■■■■4h■4h4h4■4h4
and this is the Lowe's
"Do it Wright Playbook."
Why don't you break down this
kids technique for us, Matt.
Sure thing Jay.
Lawn care is all
about the ■■
See how he starts the tr en c1
That stops that shrub
from casting a shadow
on it's bottom leaves.
He is trima high
level and he knows it.
If there was a scholarship
for landscaping,w■
I'd sign thist■■ 2 2B2
FIRST SEGMENT THE FINAL FOUR IS
TOMORROW.
OUR GREAT FRIEND JAY BILAS JOINS
US WITH HIS EXPENSIVE NEW TIE WE
HEARD ABOUT OFF AIR.
AUBURN LOST A PLAYER AND STILL
BEAT KENTUCKY.
IS THIS A ONE-SHOT DEAL OR CAN
THEY SUSTAIN THAT WITHOUT HIM?
■k HIM THEY STILL
WOUND UP WINNING THE GAME, BUT
HE WOULD HAVE BEEN A PERFECT
DEFENDER TO PUT ON DEANDRE
HUNTER OF VIRGINIA, A LOTTERY
PICK, THE MOST DIFFICULT TO
DEFEND.
MIKE: IT'S LOSING A LOT.
VIRGINIA, JAY, AS YOU KNOW, IS
VERY DELIBERATE.
AUBURN IS UP-TEMPO TO SAY THE
LEAST.
DOES ANYBODY HAVE AN ADVANTAGE
WHEN IT COMES TO TEMPO AND COULD
YOU SEE ONE OF THOSE TEAMS
FORCING ITS WILL ON THE OTHER?
JAY: YEAH.
I THINK IT'S MORE LIKELY,
MICHAEL, TO BE VIRGINIA, SORT OF
THE OLD AXIOM ARE IT'S EASIER TO
SLOW A GAME DOWN THAN SPEED ONE
UP.
VIRGINIA PLAYS MOST OF OF ITS
GAMES AT ITS TEMPO.
'S HARD TO GET THEM TO PLAY
FASTER.
WE'LL SEE THIS GAME PLAYED AT A
SLOWER PACE.
ONE OF THE THINGS ABOUT
VIRGINIA, VIRGINIA PLAYS A
PACKED LINE DEFENSE THAT GETS A
LOT OF DISCUSSION, BUT WHEN THEY
PUT UP A SHOT, THEYREE
■y■=>z6yR; BUT THEY'LL HAVE
TO GET BACK AND DEFEND THE
THREE-POINT LINE.
USUALLYY'RE DEFENDING THE
r■ AND BUILD BACK OUT.
TONY: ABOUT A YEAR AGO, IT
LOOKED LIKE BRUCE PEARL COULD
LOSE HIS JOB AT AUBURN.
WHAT DO YOU THINK HIS THINKING
NOW?
JAY: I THINK HE'S THINKING HE
NEEDS TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THIS,
THAT BRUCE PEARL HAS HAD A LOT
OF THINGS GO ON IN HIS CAREER,
ALL THE WAY BACK TO THE DION
THOMAS STUFF WHEN HE WAS AN
ASSISTANT TO TOM DAVIS, HAD THE
ACCUSATIONS AND TAPE WITH
ILLINOIS, CHEATING, ALL THAT
STUFF, AND HE WAS OUT OF THE
GAME.
HE WAS OUT OF THE GAME FOR A
SHOW CAUSE ABOUT REALLY A
BARBECUE AND NOT BEING
FORTHCOMING TO THE NCAA.
HE'S GOT A WONDERFUL OPPORTUNITY
AND HAS A GOOD TEAM.
WITH ALL THE STUFF HANGING OVER
COLLEGE SPORTS -- AND HONESTLY,
IT'S NOT JUST COLLEGE
BASKETBALL, IT'S IN OTHER AREAS
AS WELL -- NOBODY CARES.
LIKE NOBODY CARES.
YOU JUST KEEP PLAYING, MAN.
THIS IS GOING TO -- THERE ARE
GOING TO BE PEOPLE CAUGHT UP IN
THIS WHOLE■= F LOSE
THEIR JOBS, BUT THEñ2 TRUTH IS
FANS DON'T CARE.
MIKE: LET'S GO TO THE LATE GAME
BETWEEN TEXAS TECH AND MICHIGAN
STATE.
REGGIE MILLER WENT TO A TEXAS
TECH PRACTICE, AND HE SAID IT
WAS THE BEST PRACTICE HE HAD
EVER SEEN, WHICH LEADS ME TO ASK
YOU WHAT IS CHRIS BEARD DOING
THAT OTHERS ARE NOT?
JAY: I DON'T KNOW THAT HE'S
DOING ANYTHING THAT OTHERS ARE
NOT, BUT CHRIS IS A REALLY GOOD
COACH.
THEY RUN GOOD STUFF.
HE'S A BOB KNIGHT DISCIPLE IN A
LOT OF DIFFERENT WAYS, HE'S HAD
DIFFERENT MENTORS, BUT BOB
KNIGHT THE MOST INFLUENTIAL.
HE RUNS A LOT OF MOTION OFFENSE,
WHERE THEY HAVE ROOM TO CUT.
ALL THE CUTTERS AND THEIR
SCREENING ACTION, THE CUTTERS
ARE GOING TO THE BALL OR TO THE
BASKET.
IT'S REALLY DIFFICULT TO GUARD.
IT'S DIFFICULT TO SCOUT.
AND THEN HE -- I THINK HE HAS
FUN.
THEY'RE VERY SERIOUS ABOUT THE
WAY THEY GO ABOUT THEIR
BUSINESS, BUT AFTER THEIR
S DONE THEY DECIDE
THEY'RE GOING TO ENJOY
THEMSELVES AND HAVE4■I0■■ THINKG
FUN IS DOING HARD THINGS WELL, A
MANTRA THAT TEXAS TECH HAS HAD.
A BUNCH OF COACHES OUT■■#■#■#■#F
YAHOO!, AND HE SAID MICHIGAN
STATE IS THE BEST TEAM HERE.
WITH THAT IN MIND, I'LL ASK YOU,
WOULD YOU BE SURPRISED IF ANYONE
ELSE WON THIS TOURNAMENT?
JAY: NO, I WOULD NOT BE
SURPRISED.
LOOK, MICHIGAN STATE MAY VERY
WELL BE THE BEST TEAM.
COMING INTO THIS, I RANKED
VIRGINIA AHEAD OF MICHIGAN
STATE.
NOT ONLY WERE THEY A NUMBER ONE
SEED, THEY'VE ONLY LOST THREE
GAMES ALL YEAR LONG.
VIRGINIA IS THE REAL DEAL.
I HAPPEN TO THINK IT'S MICHIGAN
STATE AND VIRGINIA IN THE FINAL,
BUT MICHIGAN STATE MATCHES UP
WELL WITH VIRGINIA.
THEY REBOUND BETTER, AND THAT'S
WHERE THEY'VE BEATEN VIRGINIA IN
THE PAST IS ON THE GLASS.
I DON'T KNOW IF THIS YEAR IT
WILL AS PRONOUNCED A DIFFERENCE,
BECAUSE THIS IS A GOOD
REBOUNDING VIRGINIA TEAM, THAT
CAN SHOOT THE BALL FROM MULTIPLE
POSITIONS.
I THINK VIRGINIA IS THE BEST
TEAM HERE, BUT FAVOR MICHIGAN
STATE TO WIN IT BECAUSE OF
TONY: THANK UCH, JAY.
MIKE: PRESSURE IT.
TONY: N■■■■#■#■#■■■#■#■■■#■■■■■z
HOW PRICEY THAT IS.
LET'S TAKE ONE LAST BREAK.
STILL TO COME, THE NEW YORK JETS
GET NEW UNIFORMS.
WILBON WILL TELL YOU WHETHER
THEY'RE A FASHION DO OR DON'T.
MIKE: TREVOR BAUER GETS YANKED
OUT OF HIS NEW OWN NO-HITTER.
TERRY FRANCONA, DID HE MAKE THE
♪♪
♪ LiMu Emu & Doug ♪
What do all these people
have in common, Limu?
[ paper rustling ]
Exactly, nothing.
They're completely
different people,
that's why they
need customized
Car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need!
[ gargling ]
[ coins hitting the desk ]
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done
it again, LiMu.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
Oh, wow. You two are going to
have such a great trip.
Thyou, we will.
This is why Voya helps reach
today's goals...
...all while helping you to and
through retirement.
Can you help with these?
We're more of the plan, invest
and protect kind of help...
Voya. Helping you to
and through retirement.
At AutoZone, batteries
are kind of our thing.
After our free tes
Atturns out she just s
arneeded new cables.g.
This guy?
Just a fresh charge.
Welcome to America's #1■■
battery destination.
Getting the job done,
just got easier.
There's little rest
for a single dad,
S and back pain made it hard to
sleep and get up on time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid,
plus the 12 hour pain
relieving strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a Better AM.
(Ariana)
What is he DOING?
■&(Vince)& aú■ó■■G■>■4.2.2■2■2
He better not be messing up
our taxes.
(Lisa)
At H&R Block, you have your own
screen so you can see your
credits, deductions and tax
tips!
(Vince)
We need that now.
(Tax Pro)
What?
(Lisa VO) ♪
Know as you go at
H&R Block.
See your credits, deductions
and tax tips.
Block has your back.
TONY: HAPPY 46TH BIRTHDAY FERRED
TRAINED FASHION DESIGNER.
HIS SONG A COUPLE YEARS "HAPPY"
WAS NOMINATED FOR AN OSCAR.
HE HAS THE GIANTS SMOKEY THE
BEAR HAT.
SPORTS CONNECTION DUBIOUS, BUT
"P.T.I." CONNECTION, HE DROPPED
OUT OF NORTHWESTERN, REALIZING
THERE WAS A BETTER LIFE BY FAR
AND WENT DIRECTLY INT■po■■■ñ■ñ■■
MIKE: NORTHWESTERN'S OWN.
TONY: NOT SO HAPPY ANNIVERSARY
CHRIS WEBBER.
26 YEARS AGO ON THIS DAY WEBER
CALLED FOR A TIME-OUT WHICH
MICHIGAN DIDN'T HAVE, WHICH DREW
A TECHNICAL, SEALING THE VICTORY
FOR DEAN SMITH AND NORTH
CAROLINA TO WIN A TITLE.
THE FINE PLAYER AND ANNOUNCER,
BUT THE RINGS WE THOUGHT HE
WOULD GET HAVE ESCAPED HIM.
MIKE: ONE■ñ■ñññ■■
HIM, THE ONE SACRAMENTO WOULD
HAVE HSE THEY OUTPLAYED
THE LAKERS IN THAT POSTSEASON.
YOU KNOW THAT.
TONY: HAPPY TRAILS TO THE JETS
UNIFORMS.
THE NEW UNIFORMS ARE A BRIGHTER
GREEN THAN THE OLD ONES.
THE THEIR HELMETS ARE GREEN AS
WELL.
THE AS SOMEONE WHO GREW UP
LOVING THE JETS, THE CLASSIC
SIMPLICITY OF THEIR UNIFORMS,
THESE UNIFORMS
ARE YOU GOING TO GREEN HELMETS?
MIKE: THAT LOOKS LIKE THE GREEN
VERSION OF WHAT THE CLEVELAND
BROWNS ARE DOING.
THAT'S HIDEOUS.
TONY: JOE MADDON'S WIN TOTAL
WITHUBS,■■■■■ 9■■tt■■■■■ñ■■■7,■A
SIX-YEAR DEAL TOGGGG
VANDERBILT.
MIKE: I THINK HE'LL BE A
TERRIFIC COACH.
TREVOR BAUER GOT PULLED AFTER
SEVEN NO-HIT INNINGS.
HE WAS OKAY.
ARE YOU?
TONY: I HAD RATHER ■n'■3g'n'n■n?
MIKE: NOT REALLY.
MIKE: SHAKA SMART'S TEAM WON THE
N.I.T.
TONY:■■■ WOMEN'S FINAL FOUR
TONIGHT.
OREGON AGAINST BAYLOR.
UCONN AND NOTRE DAME.
WHO YOU GOING WITH?
MIKE: I'M GOING WITH UCONN
VERSUS BAYLOR INAL.
TONY: