THE GAME FOR A LONG TIME.
LEADING IN REBOUNDING FOR MUCH
OF THE YEAR AND HE GAVE THEM
BIG-TIME MINUTES FOR TONY
BENNETT, THEY GET THE FIRST
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP IN SCHOOL
HISTORY IN THE MEN'S TOURNAMENT
D ALSO WINNING THE■ FIRST ONE
VIRGINIA AND■ THE A.C.C., E OF ;
THAT'S NOW THEIRNATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIPú■
THE RECORD.
WE'LL HEAR FROM THE COACHES A
LITTLE BIT LATER ON IN
"SPORTSCENTER."
BOTH CHRIS BEARD AND TEXAS TECH
AND TONY BENNETT WINNING HIS
FIRST CHAMPIONSHIP.
TALKED TO TONY YESTERDAY ABOUT
WHAT THE FEELING HE ANTICIPATED
IT WOULD BE LIKE GOING UP THAT
LADDER TO CUT DOWN THE NET.
SAID HE WOULD THINK ABOUT HIS
FAMILY.
YOU GUYS MENTIONED DIRK BENNETT
BEING THERE.
THEY TODAY A PICTURE OF HIM IN
THE STANDS.
I'M NOT SURE HE WAS ACTUALLY
WATCHING THE GAME.
THE NEW CONFERENCE OF
CHAMPIONSHIPS WITH ITS FIFTH
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP.
FOLLOWED BY THE S.E.C. AND THE
BIG 10.
ONE NOTE DOES STAY INTACT.
NO TEAM HAS EVER WON HIS -- IT'S
FIRST TIME IN THE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP BUT TEXAS TECH WAS
OH, SO CLOSE.
AND I THINK THE RESILIENCE THEY
SHOWED THROUGHOUT THE TOURNAMENT
AND IN THIS GAME.
HISTORICALLY WE'VE ALWAYS SAID
IF VIRGINIA GETS UP BY 10, IT'S
LIKE BEING UP BY 20 FOR OTHER
TEAMS.
IT WASN'T THE CASE IN THIS
TOURNAMENT.
THEY WERE ABLE TO ANSWER EVERY
TIME.
JAY W.: WHEN YOU HEAR THAT
PHRASE CALM IS CONTAGIOUS, THAT
TRANSLATES TO THE TEAM.
THEY NEVER SEEM RUSHED.
TAI WAS JUST CALM AND HE SAW THE
FACT THAT THE DEFENSE COB
TRACTED.
KICKED IT OUT TO DE' ANDRE
HUNTER.
THEY JUST MAKE THE RIGHT PLAYS.
SOME PEOPLEHERE'S AN
ELEMENT OF LUCK BUT YOU HAVE TO
PUT YOURSELF IN POSITION TO GET
THAT ELEMENT OF LUCK.
SETH: YOU SAW THE MA WHICH YOU
REMEMBER THE OF THE VIRGINIA
TEAM EVERY TIME THEIR BACK WAS
AGAINST THE WALL.
WE SAW TY JEROME AGAINST AUBURN
SETTLE LAST -- LATE CLOCK.
WE SAW HIM TODAY PLAY FROM THAT
EXPERIENCE AND ATTACK DOWNHILL.
BUT THE MA CLURLT AND POISE OF
THIS VIRGINIA TEAM IN EVERY
ADVE SITUATION, TO ME,
THROUGHOUT THE TOURNAMENT --
THIS WIL■■E THE FEWEST
ANY TEA HAS WON A
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP BY.
SNIRD ST. IVES?
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
BUT THEY'RE POISED EVERY TIME
THEIR BACK WAS AGAINST IF WALL.
A GREAT TRIBUTE TO EVERYTHING
VIRGINIA BASKETBALL STANDS FOR.
JAY B.: THEIR EXECUTION AT THE
END OF A SHOT CLOCK.
THEY LIVE FOR THE END OF THE
SHOT CLOCK.
NOTHING SEEMS TO WORRY THEM.
THEY DON'T GET RUSHED AND THEY
PLAY QUICKLY.
I THINK TONY BENNETT CALLED IT
PATIENT FLOW AND THEY WERE
EXTRAORDINARY THEIR PATIENT
WHILE STILL PROBING AND LOOKING
TO ATTACK ALL THE TIME.
JEROME IS A GREAT PLAYER.
JUST A GREAT PLAYER.
PLAYS AT DIFFERENT SPEEDS.
HE CAN SEE OVER WITH YOU THAT
SIZE.
HE'S GOT THAT RUNNER, FLOATER --
FLOATER, CAN MAKE THREES AND
CHALLENGE IN FRONT OF YOU.
I THOUGHT HE WAS TERRIFIC AT
CONTROLLING THE PACE OF THE GAME
THROUGHOUT.
HE REBOUNDED WELL.
HAD EIGHT ASSISTS AND ONLY
COUGHED IT■■■■■■■P ONE TIME AGA
THAT DEFENSE?
THAT'S OUTSTANDING.
RECE: OKLAHOMA CIT■8
MINNESOTA HERE IN TOWN YESTERDAY
AND BILLY DONOVAN HAS WON TWO
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIPS AND BILLY
DONOVAN MADE A COMMENT THAT HE
THOUGHT EVERYTHING WOULD BE
DIFFERENT ONCE HE WON A NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP AND IT REALLY
WASN'T.
AS YOU SAID PRE-GAME IT PUTS ALL
YOUR ACCOMPLISHMENTS IN A
DIFFERENT LIGHT BUT BILLY SAID
YOU UNDERSTAND THINGS YOU
ACCOMPLISHED AS A GROUP FLAW
COULDN'T ACCOMPLISH BY YOURSELF.
VIRGINIA IS UNDERSTANDING THAT
PROBABLY AS WELL AS YOU CAN
RIGHT NOW, GIVEN THAT LOSE LAST
YEAR IN THE 1-16 LOSS.
TO LOSE IN THE ROUND OF 64 AND
COME BACK AND WIN THE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP AND NONE OF THE
OTHER THREE DID IT QUITE LIKE
THE HOOVES DID.
KENNY: THE SHELL THAT WOULD LOSS
IS OFF THEM.
THE BALTIMORE COUNTY LOSS IS OFF
THEM.
ZUBIN: THEY WERE A NUMBER ONE
SEED BUT THEY DID NOT FACE A ONE
OR A TWO ON THEIR WAY TO THE
CHAMPIONSHIP.
KENNY: UNLV BEING THE LAST TO
FULL THAT OFF.
ZUBIN: ON THE WAY, A PROUD TONY
BENNETT, AND THE DISAPPOINTMENT
OF CHRIS BEARD.
BUT THE ANTY THINKS IS --
KENNY: THE KIDS BACK THERE IN
VIRGINIA CELEBRATING.
WE'RE GOING TO
So I can buy from
Enterprise Car Sales and you'll
take ANY trade-in?
That's right!
Great!
Here you go...
Well, it does need
to be a vehicle.
But - I need this out of
my house.
(VO) With fair, transparent
value for every trade-in...
Enterprise makes it easy.
WE DON'T JUST MAKE CARS...
WE MAKE TECHNOLOGY
THAT MOVES PEOPLE
♪
THIS IS THE 2019 NISSAN ROGUE
FEATURING TECH LIKE
PROPILOT ASSIST
IT HELPS KEEP YOU
CENTERED IN YOUR LANE
♪
AND IN CONTROL
THIS IS HOW NISSAN INTELLIGENT
MOBILITY IS REINVENTING DRIVING-
FOR EVERYONE.
NOW THE MOST EXCITING TECH YOU
OWN IS IN YOUR DRIVEWAY
Low battery sound.
Do you ■11■■-■■■■))
want a charge?
Yeah
Battery charging.
♪♪
Thank you So Much.
Battery charging.
♪♪
KENNY: VIRGINIA WAS KNOCKED OUT
IN THE FIRST ROUND LAST YEAR IN
THE TOURNAMENT AS A ONE SEED.
THEY COME ALL THE WAY THROUGH
THIS TIME AND IN OVERTIME TAKE
DOWN TEXAS TECH 85- 7 IN
OVERTIME.
FOR THE FIRST TIME, VIRGINIA,
NATIONAL CHAMPS OF MEN'S COLLEGE
BASKETBALL.
FULL COVERAGE THE REST OF THIS
HOUR ON THE "SPORTSCENTER."
YOU'LL HEAR FROM THE COACHES,
PROGRAM PLAYERS, STUDENT
MANAGERS IF THEY HAVE A RELEVANT
THING TO OFFER AND ALL■÷&÷■■■■ú
INTERESTING THINGS.
INCLUDING --
ZUBIN: THE■■TIME GAME   IN THE L
TONIGHT.=
2008.
MARIO CHALMERS FOR THE TIEAw/ F
KANSAS,@@ OVERTIME.
KANSAS WAS DOWN NINE WITH:1 TO■
AND WIN.
EY TAKE IT IN 2008 FOR BILL
SELF.
THAT WAS THE BIG 12 BEING
VICTORIOUS.
THE ONLY BIG 12 TEAM, BY THE
WAY, THAT HAS WON AN NCAA
CHAMPIONSHIP SINCE THE LEAGUE
WAS FORMED A LITTLE OVER 20
YEARS AGO.
TONIGHT THE BIG 12 TEAM GOES
DOWN.
OVERTIME NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP
GAME?
THERE WAS A TRIPLE OVERTIME GAME
IN 195  WHERE NORTH CAROLINA
KNOCKED OFF KANSAS, IF YOU'RE
OLD ENOUGH TO REMEMBER THAT ONE.
15TH A.C.C. TITLE FOR VIRGINIA.
NORTH CAROLINA, ONE OF THEIR
FIVE TITLES BACK IN 1957 AS
WELL.
REMEMBER THE UMBY TWITTER FIELD?
THEY WERE SNARKY LAST YEAR.
KENNY: VERY CLASSY THIS TIME
AROUND.
ZUBIN: NO DOUBT.
TWEETING THIS -- WHAT AN
INCREDIBLE SEASON FOR U.V.A.
THAT WAS TRULY A TURNAROUND FOR
THE AGES.
ONE MORE TO DECIDE IT ALL, CHRIS
BEARD, ONE GAME SHORT.
FIRST FINAL FOUR ENDS IN BITTER
DISAPPOINTMENT.
>> FIRST I JUST WANT TO
CONGRATULATE VIRGINIA BASKETBALL
AND COACH BENNETT AND TELL THEM
HOW MANY RESPECT WE HAVE FOR
THEIR PROGRAM.
THE GAME WAS EVERYTHING WE
THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
THOUGHT IT WOULD COME DOWN TO
ONE LAST POSSESSION AND IT DID
IN REGULATION AND THEN IN
OVERTIME IT JUST GOT AWAY FROM
US A LITTLE BIT.
NOTHING BUT RESPECT FOR THEIR
PROGRAM, THEIR COACHES, THEIR
PLAYERS, THEIR FANS.
I THOUGHT IT WAS A GREAT
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP GAME IN
TERMS OF OUR PLAYERS, I'VE NEVER
BEEN MORE PROUD OF A TEAM THAT
I'VE COACHED.
I THINK WHAT THESE GUYS HAVE
ACCOMPLISHED THIS YEAR.
BIG 12 CHAMPIONSHIP, FINAL FOUR,
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
WE'LL GRADUATE ALL FIVE SENIORS
HERE IN A COUPLE MONTHS AND
THESE GUYS WILL GO ON TO BE
GREAT PROS AND FATHERS AND
HUSBANDS.
NEVER BEEN MORE PROUD OF A
GROUP.
A LOT OF EMOTION IN OUR LOOKER
ROOM RIGHT NOW AND IT'S REAL.
GUYS THAT CARE ABOUT THE GUY
NEXT TO THEM BUT THIS IS LIFE
AND WE'LL BOUNCE BACK.
IN TERMS OF TEXAS TECH
BASKETBALL, WE'RE NOT GOING
ANYWHERE.
WE'LL BE BACK IN THIS TOURNAMENT
SOONER THAN LATER AND WE INTEND
TO BE A PART OF COLLEGE
BASKETBALL AS WE BUILD THE
PROGRAM.
>> WE'LL TAKE QUESTIONS FOR THE
STUDENT ATHLETES.
FACE-OFF QUESTION PLEASE RAISE
YOUR LAND?
LET'S START IN THE BACK.
>> THIS QUESTION IS FOR NOR
REPUBLICANS.
I GUESS JUST IN THAT --
NORRENCE.
IN THOSE LAST COUPLE OF MINUTES,
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
>> I THOUGHT WE NEEDED THREE.
WE NEEDED A STOP TO WIN THE
GAME.
THEY CAME DOWN, HIT A THREE TO
TIE THE GAME, SO
>> YARET -- JASHTE, WHAT KIND OF
CHALLENGE DID YOU HAVE TONIGHT
BEING GUARDED BY HUNTER FOR A
LOT OF THE GAME AND THEN ON THE
LAST POSSESSION WERE YOU
THINKING THREE THE WHOLE WAY
THERE?
>> HE'S A GREAT PLAYER.
HE PLAYED WELL TONIGHT.
I GOT THE SWITCH, I SAW THE
OPENING AND I TOOK THE SHOT.
>> JARRETT, WHEN YOU WENT INTO
OVERTIME, DID YOU FEEL LIKE YOU
HAD OVERTIME TILL -- MOMENTUM
GOING INTO THAT?
>> YEAH, WE FOR SURE FELT LIKE
WE HAD MOMENTUM.
HE SAID IT WAS JUST A
FIVE-MINUTE GAME.
WE PREPARED FOR IT EVERY DAY.
>> CONTINUING WITH QUESTIONS FOR
NORENSE OR JARRETT.
>> N OFFENSE RENSE, JUST FOR
YOU, WHAT DO YOU FEEL THE STORY
IS OF THIS TEAM?
I KNOW IT'S LITTLE TIME REMOVED
FROM IT BUT WHAT DO YOU WANT THE
STORY TO BE FOR THIS TEAM?
>> RESILIENCE AND TOUGHNESS,
EVERYTHING WE ARE AT A -- AS A
TEAM.
IT TOOK A LOT TO GET HERE.
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT
TOGETHER.
TO GET HERE IT TOOK A LOT OF
GUTS AND I'M PROUD FOR OUR TEAM
FOR THAT BUT IT DOESN'T FEEL
GOOD AT ALL RIGHT NOW.
>> CONTINUING WITH QUESTIONS FOR
THE TEXAS TECH STUDENT ATHLETES,
IF THERE ARE ANY.
TOWARD THE CENTER OF THE ROOM.
>> JARKTSE DID WE SEE YOU PLAY
YOUR LAST GAME TONIGHT AS A RED
RAIDER OR IS THAT DECISION STILL
TO BE MADE?
>> THAT DECISION IS STILL TO BE
MADE.
ALL SEASON I JUST FOCUSED ON MY
TEAM AND TRYING TO WIN A
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP SO I
HAVEN'T THOUGHT ABOUT THAT ANY.
NOW THAT THE SEASON IS OVER I'LL
TAKE TIME WITH MY FAMILY AND
COACH AND CONSIDER MY FUTURE.
>> CONTINUING WITH QUESTIONS FOR
JARRETT AND NORENSE, IF THERE
ARE ANY.
WE'D LIKE TO THANK THEM FOR
JOINING US HERE IN THE MAIN
INTERVIEW ROOM.
THEY'RE GOING TO HEAD BACK TO
THE LOCKER ROOM.
CONGRATULATIONS, FELLOWS, ON A
GREAT SEASON AND A GREAT RUN.
FIRST QUESTION FOR COACH BEARD,
PLEASE RAISE YOUR HAND IF YOU
HAVE ONE.
LET'S GO UP FRONT TO THE RIGHT.
DAN.
>> HI.
U.S.A. TODAY.
HUNTER MADE THAT THREE IN THE
CORNER TO TIE THE GAME AT THE
END OF REGULATION.
IT LOOKED LIKE I SAW YOU
MOTIONING.
WERE YOU TRYING TO SAY NO THREES
THERE?
YOU MADE A MOTION TO YOUR TEAM.
>> WHEN WE WERE ON OFFENSE OR
DEFENSE?
>> YOU GUYS WERE ON DEFENSE.
>> YEAH, WE WORK ON THAT EVERY
DAY IN PRACTICE.
THREE-POINT LEAD.
WE DON'T WANT TO GIVE UP A THREE
SO -- BUT I TRUST MY PLAYERS.
WE WORK ON IT EVERY SINGLE DAY.
I'LL HAVE TO GO BACK AND WATCH
THE FILM.
IT LOOKED LIKE SOME DRIBBLE
PENETRATION, MAYBE BASELINE AND
A REALLY GOOD PASS BUT YEAH, IN
THAT SITUATION WITH A
THREE-POINT LEAD AND LESS THAN A
SHOT CLOCK LEFT, WE'RE TRYING TO
PLAY REALLY SOUND DEFENSE WITH
NO THREE-POINT SHOTS NO, AND
ONES AND WE HAVE TO SECURE THE
DEFENSIVE REBOUND.
WE JUST CAME UP A LITTLE BIT
SHORT BUT GIVE VIRGINIA CREDIT.
THEY'RE A REALLY, REALLY GOOD
TEAM.
SO MUCH POISE AND I JUST HAVE A
LOT OF RESPECT FOR THEM.
KENNY: DISAPPOINTMENT EXPRESSED
IN THEIR FACES AND IN THEIR
ANSWERS THERE.
TEXAS TECH WENT TO THE TITLE.
GOES DOWN AGAINST VIRGINIA.
KNOWN FOR ITS DEFENSE ALL
SEASON.
THROUGH THE FIRST FOUR GAMES.
OPPONENTS SCORED JUST 65 ON
AVERAGE.
THEY ALSO GAVE UP 11 THREES
AFTER ALLOWING UNDER SIX IN THE
FIRST FIVE GAMES.
RECE DAVIS AND THE CREW.
RECE: THAT 40% SHOOTING THAT
TEXAS TECH ALLOWED, THE SECOND
BEST BY AN OPPONENT THIS SEASON
AND JARRETT CULVER STRUGGLED,
LARGELY DUE TO THE VIRGINIA
DEFENSE.
HE MISSED 17 SHOTS, THE MOST
CHAMPIONSHIP GAME SINCE 19  5.
VIRGINIA EASE DEFENSE HAD A LOT
TO DO WITH THAT.
JAY B.: VIRGINIA'S DEFENSE IS
EXCELLENT.
IT HAS BEEN ALL SEASON.
I THOUGHT KIHEI CLARK DID A
GREAOUT■>■■■
MOONEY.■■■■O■YTIME HE TRIED TO
THE PRE WAS A DOUBLE
ISOLATION THAT GOT IT OUT OF HI■
■■[ GREAT TURN OONLED
JUMPER.
THAT WAS ABOUT IT.
BUT THE INDIVIDUAL PERFORMANCE
THAT STOOD OUT WAS HUNTER ON
CULVER.
HUNTER IS THE A.C.C. PLAYER
TOOST YEAR AND HE VALIDATEED
THAT AND THEN SOME.
FOR HIM TO PLAY ON BOTH ENDS AT
THE LEVEL HE PLAYED, THAT'S MOST
OUTSTANDING PLAYER STUFF AND
LEGENDARY STUFF.
27 POINTS, NINE REBOUNDS AND
HOLD Aéá POTENTIALéá LOTTERY PIN
CULVER■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
SETH:■UN■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
THE■■■■■■■■ HELP OF■?■■■/■í■á■■.
THEIR GAME PLAN WAS WHO THEY
WERE BUT DEANDRE HUNTER, HIS
IMPRINT ON THE GAME.
LET'S FACE IT.
DOWN THE STRETCH,■■TECH■■ ■GOIN
OFF, THE BALL WAS■■■ GOING TO BN
CULVER'S HANDS.
LIKE IT WAS AT THE END  THE
OTHER NIGHT SO THEIR ABILITY TO
TAKE HIM OUT WAS HUGE.
THE END OF THE GAME, YOU CANNOT
HELP OFF CORNER AND THAT PLAY
ADVERSITY.AY AT THE END■■■■■■■■
IT'S ONE OF THE BEST STORIES I
THINK EVER IN■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■T
IN THAT SITUATION FO■■■■■■■■■■■H
CLASS.
BUT FOR THIS TEAM TO WIN THE BIG
12 AFTER KANSAS HAS DOMINATED
GOING ON 14 YEARS, FOR THEM TO
LOSE IN A BIG 123 TOURNAMENT TO
WEST VIRGINIA, TO BOUNCE BACK
THE WAY THEY DID IN THE NCAA
TOURNAMENT, THEY'VE HAD A
TREMENDOUS YEAR.
RECE: LOST FIVE OF THEIR TOP SIX
SCORERS FROM A YEAR AGO.
THEY'VE WON AS MANY NCAA
TOURNAMENT GAMES AS Y HAVE IN
THEIR ENTIRE PROGRAM.
THAT CORNER, IF MEMORY SERVES,
THAT'S THE SAME CORNER KYLE GUY
HIT THE THREE AGAINST AUBURN
TOO.
THERE WAS ONE PLAY IN OVERTIME
AND IT'S GOTTEN SOME ATTENTION.
FROM MY POINT OF VIEW, THE
OFFICIALS, WHEN THEY WENT TO THE
MONITOR TO SEE IF IT WASUT OF
BOUNDS AND VIRGINIA WAS AWARDED
THE BALL.
I THOUGHT THEY GOT THE CALL■■■■
CALL RILINGTE RIGHT AS WELL.
SETH: IT WAS A HECK OF AN FIRST
QUARTERED GAME.
THERE'S NONONE PLAY YOU SAY
WHAT.
IF
JAY W.: FIRST TIME I'VE HEARD ■.
JAY B.: I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS
ARE COMPLAINING ABOUT THE
OFFICIATING.
RECE: 85-77, JUST THE WAY
EVERYBODY HAD IT DRAWN UP.
TOOK THEM A WHILE TO GET GOING
OFFENSIVELY BUT MAN, WHAT A
GAME.
VIRGINIA IS THE NATIONAL
CHAMPION.
KENNY: SOME OF YOU DEBATE SEE
THE WHOLE GAME.
YOU WERE TOO BUSY WATCHING
BASEBALL HIGHLIGHTS WITH US.
TEXAN, CULVER MINIATURE.
DRIVING.
JUST 5-22 FROM THE FLOOR
THAT WAS BIG.
TECH WITH THE LEAD.
IA DOWN THREE, UNDER 20 TO
GO.
KICK TO THE CORNER.
DEANDRE HUNTER, THANK YOU FOR MY
LIFE, TIES THE GAME.
HUNTER T THREE.
TIED AT 6 -6 .
CULVER, LONG JUMPER.1ALF.
NOT GOOD.
HE WAS TRYING TIME-OUT  CK OUT E
BUT THE PASS WENT THROUGH
OUT OF BOUNDS SO ONE SECOND,
THEY GOT A PLAY BUT THE SHOT IS
REDACTED BYRAXTON KEY.
OVERTIME■é#■■á á ARY.
FIRST TIME SINCE 2008.
HUNTERUT ONE IN THE AIR.
SAME SPOT.
HEe■e■e■e■■■t■ 27 IN THIS ONE.ql
■■■■é■INIA IS  75-73.
JEROME DRIVE@p■h MISSES.
BALL IS WAY OUT■ FRONT.
SCRAM FBLE FOR IT.
POKED AWAY.
WHOSE BALL?
NOW WE HAVE TO LOOK AT THE MONO
FIGURE -- MONITOR FOR 10, 15 --
IT'S OVERTURNED AND GIVEN TO
VIRGINIA OFF HIS■■ FINGERNAIL.
JEROME COMING TO THE RACK.
DRAWLS THE FOUL.
WE BELIEVE THE INSIDE.
AND SIMILARLY, IN THEIR
SEMIFINAL GAME FREE THROWS
MATTER.
THEY HIT THEM THERE.
JEROME HITS;/x■g■g■gçW■WHE SHOO
EXTEND THE LEAD IN THIS CASE.
ANOTHER TOUGH CALL ON MATT
MOONEY AND VIRGINIA FOR THE
FIRST TIME IS NATIONAL CHAMPIONS
OF MEN'S NCAA BASKETBALL.
85-77 YOUR FINAL.
TEXAS TECH FOUGHT HARD TO GET
THERE.
A 31-WIN SEASON BUTñ7ñ7ñ7HEY COP
JUST SHORT.
HERE WAS AN EMOTIONAL COACH
CHRIS BEARD JUST AFTER THE
>> COACH, IT LOOKED LIKE YOU
STOPPED TO TALK TO A COUPLE OF
GUYS BEFORE YOU WALKED OFF THE
FLOOR.
WHAT WAS YOUR MESSAGE TO THEM
AFTER THE GAME THERE?
>> JUST -- PHAU!
-- PPHEW!
JUST TOLD THEM I LOVED THEM AND
OUR RELATIONSHIP IS JUST GETTING
STARTED.
I'LL BE AT THOSE GUYS' WEDDINGS
ONE DAY AND HOPEFULLY WHEN THEIR
KIDS GET BORN AND DO EVERYTHING
I CAN TO TALK THEM OUT OF
GETTING INTO COACHING SO THEY
DON'T EVER FEEL LIKE THIS BUT I
JUST LOVE THOSE GUYS.
>> IF YOU HAVE A QUESTION FOR
COACH BEARD, PLEASE RAISE YOUR
HAND.
>> COACH, ON LAST VIRGINIA
POSSESSION OF REGULATION, DID
YOU CONSIDER FOULING AT ALL AT
THE THREE?
>> I THINK THERE WERE 22 SECONDS
LEFT.
A LITTLE EARLY.
WE'VE GOT SOME CALLS.
GIVE VIRGINIA CREDIT.
IF THEY HAD COME DOWN AND RUN A
MORE DELIBERATE POSSESSION LIKE
THEY NORMALLY DO, WE WOULD HAVE
FOULED UP TOP.
WE HAVE SOME SIGNALS.
WE WERE READY FOR THAT.
TO ME, THEY GOT REAL AGGRESSIVE
AND DIDN'T HAVE A CHANCE TO DO
THAT.
WE WERE PREPARED FOR THAT.
WE WORK ON IT EVERY DAY AND I
TRUST MY PLAYERS.
I'LL ALWAYS BE A GUY THAT TRUSTS
PLAYERS.
KENNY: CRYING IS HEALTHY.
CHRIS BEARD DID SOME OF THAT
EXPRESSING HIS DEVOTION TO THE
TEAM AND HOW HE EXPRESSED
HIMSELF TO HIS TEAM AFTER A
DIFFICULT LOSS IN OVERTIME.
VIRGINIA TRAILED IN THE FINAL 20
SECOND IN THE SECOND HALF IN
EACH OF THE LAST THREE GAMES.
THEY WON ALL OF THEM AND TEXAS
TECH IN THE TITLE GAME.
ZUBIN:  FROM THE DECEMBER SPARE
OF HEARING THOSE WORDS FROM
CHRIS BEARD TO THE ELATION OF
TONY BENNETT.
WE'LL HEAR FROM HIM AND SOME
♪
♪ It is such a good time
to kiss ♪
to dance ♪
♪ It is such a good time to ♪
[ Laughing ]
♪ Scoobidoo doobidoo ♪
[ Goose honking ]
♪♪
[ Laughing ]
A bad day on the road still
beats a good one off it.
♪♪
Progressive helps keep you
out there.
♪♪
[outdoor ambiance]
♪
Hi, Mrs. Gorman.
Hey, Theo.
police radio: I have
the stolen vehicle in sight.
[police siren]
♪
xxxÑ           ♪
[police siren]
police radio: OnStar,
it's safe to slow it down.
♪
OnStar Advisor:
Mr. Grantham, this is OnStar.
The police have your vehicle.
ZUBIN: WELCOME BACK TO
"SPORTSCENTER."
A LITTLE MORE ON THE CHAMPS FOR
YOU.
VIRGINIA LOST TWO REGULAR SEASON
GAMES, BOTH TO DUKE.
SEEMS FITTING BECAUSE DUKE,
THEIR FRESHMAN AND A BLOWN
SNEAKER GOT MORE ATTENTION THAN
THE BEST COLLEGE BASKETBALL
STORY PERCOLATING ALL YEAR.
TIME TO TAKE TONY BENNETT OFF
THE BEST COACHES LIST TO NEVER
WIN A NATIONAL TIME.
HERE'S RECE DAVIS WITH MORE.?a?■
RECE:s■■■■■■ALIER ATTITUDE.
IMPLIES CAREFREE.
WHATEVER'S HAPPENED, FORGET IT.
DENIAL WASB■E FOR■
VIRGINIA.
THEIR CAVALIERTTITUDE
ION DEMANDED THEY CONFRONTOO■
THEIR ALBATROSS.
THE BURDEN OF THE MOST
HUMILIATING LOSE IN TOURNAMENT
HISTORY
>> THE ULTIMATE UPSET HAS
HAPPENED.
A 16 HAS BEAT AN ONE.
UMBC KNOCKS OFF VIRGINIA!
RECE: A STAIN THAT COULDN'T BE
ERASED, NO MATTER HOW MANY
REGULAR SEASON GAMES THEY WON,
NO MATTER HOW MANY TIMES PEOPLE
SPOKE OF REDEMPTION.
REDEMPTION IS NOT THE RIGHT
WORD.
THAT IMPLIES A CLEAN SLATE.
NOT ONLY FORGIVEN BUT FORGOTTEN
THIS STABLE COULDN'T BE ERASED.
BUT IT COULD BE MINIMIZED.
IF YOU WANT A HAPPYING THAT
DEPENDS ON WHERE YOU STOP YOUR
STORY, OR IN THE WORDS OF
ANOTHER TONY BENNETT, THE
CAVALIERS COULD GO FROM RAGS TO
RICHES IN THIS TOURNAMENT THEY
STRUGGLED WITH THE6-SEALED■#
DEMON AGAIN AND SAVED THEMSELVES
FROM ONE SEEMINGLY HOPELESS
SITUATION AFTER ANOCH
MORE DESPERATE THAN THE LAST.
>> HE GOT IT!
HE GOT I
RE'S A
SALVAGED BY STEELY EYED FREE
THROWS, THREE OF THEM FROM KYLE
GUY WHO HAD WRESTLED PUBLICLY
WITH THE PAIN OF THE LAST YEAR
AND CONQUERED IT.
>> THE CAVALIERS WILL PLAY FOR
RST NATIONAL
RECE: WHEN ONE STE■X WAS LEFT,
VIRGINIA TOOK IT.
THE VIETNAM DATING MOMENT.
RELENTLESS DEFENSE, STUBBORNLY
METHODICAL.
PROPRIATE.■IS NO QUICK FIX FOR
SOOTHING THE WOUNDS OF THE PAST
YEAR THE TONY OW NET SAID THE
BEST THING HE DID TO HELP HIS
PLAYERS THROUGH IT WAS PRAY FOR
THEM.
>> FROM RUIN TO REDEMPTION.
RGINIA DAVE LEERS ARE THE
NATIONAL CHAMPIONS.
RECE: THEIRITH AN
ASSIST FROM A HEALTHY DOSE OF
CAVALIER ATTITUDE AND A NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP.
SCOTT: WELL SAID BY RECE DAVIS.
LEADING D I IN SCORING AND
DEFENSE.
IT HAPPENED IN THE LATE NIVETS
WITH COACH NEWELL KOUL BUT WE'RE
HERE AGAIN WITH A TEAM THAT
LIVES, EATS, AND CELEBRATES A
CHAMPIONSHIP. Y:■ ■K■2■2■■■,■E■L
AND CLASSY IN DEFEAT.
I BELIEVE WE CAN EXPECT THE SAME
THING FROM VIRGINIA'S TONY
BENNETT.
EXLTED TO COME TO THE PODIUM
REAL SOON AS OUR
I'm Paige, and well the little
thing that I like about the
Grilled Chicken Sandwich is
that it's pi■,■,■,■,■,t.
It's juicy and it just has
all the right combinations.
I think I could be considered
a Grilled Chicken Sandwich
influencer.
My name is Frank and the
little thing I like
about the Grilled Chicken
Sandwich is the first bite.
I love how juicy the chicken is
but there's also the tomatoes
and the lettuce and
it's incredible.
Make sure you get it
with waffle fries,
because that's my favorite.
ZUBIN: WE ARE BACKN
"SPORTSCENTER."
ON THE WAY, HEAD COACH TONY
BENNETT AT THE BOTH PODIUM ALONG
WITH FINAL FOUR MOSTÑ7ANDINGPLA
THE SECOND THEY HIT THE MIKE,
WE'LL BRING IT TO YOU LIVE ON
"SPORTSCENTER."
KENNY: EXHILARATION, OPTIMISM
AND LET'S BRING YOU DOWN.
KHRIS DAVIS -- CHRIS DAVIS IN
THE ORIOLES.
6-88 ALL-TIME AGAINST MARCO
SECOND INNING, DAVIS GOT A LOT
OF IT BUT■@■@■@■p STEPHEN PISCO
STANDING THERE.
WAS EASY FOR HIM SO 0 FOR
HIS LAST  45.
BUT LET'S MAKE SOMETHING HAPPEN
HERE.
DAVIS TRYING TO AVOID THE
ALL-TIME STREAK, 46.
THIRD INNING, THE 0-2 PITCH.
PUTS IT IN THE AIR.
PROFAR THINKS HE HAS IT.
CHASES IT DOWN BUT DROPS IT.
LITTLE KID IN THE STANDS THOUGHT
THE BALL HAD FINALLY DROPPED BUT
NO, FOUL BALL.
0-  STILL.
SNAPPED THE OTHER WAY.
GOT HIS BAT ON IT TWICE
SHOT A COUPLE GOOD ONES BUT
GROSSMAN IS THERE FOR THE OUT
AND THE RECORD IS TIED.
0-4  OVER TWO SEASONS FOR H
NOW TRYING TO AVOID THE OUTRIGHT
RECORD IF LONGEST HITLESS
STREAK.■@■@
INSTEAD HE GET IT.
0-4, A NEW MAJOR LEAGUE RECORD.
THE BATTING ARCH LITERALLY ZERO
THIS SEASON.
DOES HAVE TWO R.B.I.
DAVIS, SITTING AT 2-4 --■p 0-47.
WATCH THIS GO BY.
NOW 0-48.
THIS IS A ROUGH PATCH.
EIGHTH INNING, HE GETS ANOTHER
TRY.
0-2 COUNT.
WE WILL SHOW THE WHOLE THING.
NOW 0-1.
HE WATCHES THAT STRIKE TWO,
HASN'T MOVED HIS BAT YET.
STAY OFF IT, DOWN LOW.
DO SOMETHING, SWING YOUR BAT.
HE DOES BUT HE MISSED.
ROUGH, ROUGH PATCH.
12-4, THE ORIOLES DID WIN THIS
BASEBALL GAME.
29 AT-BATS DURING THIS STREAK,
END IN A STRIKEOUT.
10 TIMES THE BALL HE HITS DOES
NOT EVEN LEAD THE INFIELD.
GOT TWO R.B.I.'S.
ONE ON A BASES-LOADED WALK.
ANOTHER ON A FIELDER'S CHOICE.
THE GUYS ARE BEHIND HIM.
HE'LL GET SOME MORE SWINGS,■■=■?
ZUBIN: TONY BENNETT JUST
COMPLETED HIS 10TH SEASON AT  .
B■
■@■@B[@■@■■■■ FULFILLED WHEN
WE RETURN.
TONY
♪ ♪
Plants capture CO2.
What if other kinds of p■■■■óo8
If these industrial plants had
technology■=■=■=■=■=■
that captured carbon like trees
we could help lower emissions.
Carbon Capture is important
technology -
and experts agree.
That's why we're working on ways
to improve it.
So plants...
can be a little more...
like plants.
♪ ♪
dvisor,
■s inent.
imagined your dream car   s
as something fast.
Then one day you decide
it just needs to be
safe enough to get her
to college and back.
Principal. We can help
you plan for that.
♪
(VO)
I know what you're thinking.
Electric, it's not for you.
And, you're probably right.
Electric just doesn't
have enough range.
It will never
survive the winter.
Charging stations?
Good luck finding one of those.
So, maybe an electric car
isn't for you after all.
Or, is it?
♪
I'm Paige, and well the little
thing that I like about the
Grilled Chicken Sandwi  that'.
It's juicy and it just has
all the right combinations.
I think I could be considered
a Grilled Chicken Sandwich
influencer.
My name is Frank and the
little thing I like
about the Grilled Chicken
Sandwich is the first bite.
I love how juicy the chicken is
but there's also the tomatoes
and the lettuce and
it's incredible.
Make sure you get it
with waffle fries,
because that's my favorite.
♪♪
The Home Depot's making it easy
to turn your favorite moment...
into the perfect color to
transform your room
with the ProjectColor app.
Explore the most popular colors
and trending palettes
to find yours.
Get a colorful new experience
with the ProjectColor app...
...then get everything you'll
need,
at your destination for the best
brands...
The Home Depot. More Saving.
More Doing.
♪♪
It's the
first day of school.
Yeah, he's so nervous.
Tom is letting him kno wil.
■
I know, it's a big day.
■■B■BBB■I'm so proud of him.
Gotta go.
♪♪
Good luck on
your first day.
Just as we help companies
advance in the digital era,
Cognizant is helping
people do the same,
by investing in skills training
in communities nationwide.
♪♪
NOT SUPPOSED TO TALK, NEVER
MIND.
>> YEAH, IT WAS A GREAT PLAY.
HE DREW IT UP.
ZUBIN: LIVE ON "SPORTSCENTER,"
THE CHAMPIONS HAVE ARRIVED.
>> WE WERE RUNNING ACTION AND I
THOUGHT WE'D GET IT.
SORRY.
>> THE THREE, YOU HIT THE SAME
THING IN OVERTIME.
>> IT WASREAT PASS AND GREAT
SHOT.
(8R] 8>> WE'RE A LITTLE CONFUSE
WHICH PLAY YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
>> MAYBE WE'LL GET BACK TO IT.
LET'S GO TO THE RIGHT OF THE
AISLE.
MIKE.
>> KYLE AND TY, A YEAR AGO
SITTING AT THE PODIUM, THE
EMOTIONS YOU FELT.
TO BE HERE NOW AS THE NATIONAL
CHAMPION, CAN  TRY TO
PUT INTO WORDS WHAA
EL RIGHT NOW?
>> MIKE, WHO WAS THAT FIRST?
TY FIRST, PLEASE, THEN KYLE.
>> I WAS GOING TO SAY DON'T ASK
ME.
FORGET LAST YEAR.
THIS IS EVERYTHING YOU DREAM OF
SINCE YOU'RE A LITTLE KID.
I'M NOT EVEN THINKING ABOUT UMBC
RIGHT NOW.
I'M JUST THINKING THIS IS A
DREAM COME TRUE AND IT'S EVEN
MORE THAN THAT BECAUSE YOU NEVER
IMAGINE YOU'LL BE ABLE TO SPEND
A YEAR WITH PEOPLE YOU ACTUALLY
LOVE.
YOUR TEAMMATES AND YOUR COACHES.
NOT A LOT OF PEOPLE GET ALONG
LIKE WE DO.
SO TO SHARE THIS MOMENT WITH
THEM IS UNBELIEVABLE.
>> KYLE?
>> YEAH, WE CAME IN TOGETHER AND
SAID THAT WE WERE GOING TO WIN A
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP AND TO BE
ABLE TO HUG EACH OTHER WITH
CONFETTI GOING EVERYWHERE AND
SAY WE DID IT, IT'S THE GREATEST
FEELING I'VE EVER FELT IN
BASKETBALL.
>> NANCY?
>> USA TODAY SPORTS.
KYLE, HAVE YOU CHANGED YOUR
SCREEN SETTING OR YOUR AVATAR?
>> I'LL GET AROUND TO IT.
>> WHEN YOU WERE WRITING THE
LETTERS, DID YOU VISUALIZE IN
YOUR MIND GOING FROM THAT TO
THIS AND HOW CLOSELY DOES IT
RESEMBLE THAT IF YOU DID?
>> YEAH, I THINK EVERYONE ON THE
SOON AS THE BUZZER
SOUNDED AND WE WERE DONE WITH
THE PRESS CONFERENCE AND STUFF.
WE KNEW WE ALL HAD THE SAME GOAL
IN MIND FOR NEXT YEAR AND THAT
WAS TO WIN THE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP.
YOU KNOW, WE'VE ALL HAD OUR OWN
BATTLES AND I SAID EARLIER THAT
IT'S A REALLY SPECIAL GROUP
BECAUSE WE ALL HAD THE SAME WHY
BUT TO SHARE THE SAME ONE AND
BATTLE AND COME OUT ON TOP IS A
FANTASTIC FEELING.
>> JEFF?
>> YOU SAID TO ME THAT WHEN YOU
GOT BACK TO CAM PUT LAST TIME,
YOU HAD THE HOOD ON, HEAD DOWN.
WHAT'S IT GOING TO BE LIKE NOW?
WHAT IS THIS ALL LIKE FOR YOU
RIGHT NOW?
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN SHED A TEAR.
HAVE ANY OF YOU SHE WOULD A TEAR
YET?
>> I DID.
>> YOU DID?
THE OTHER TWO VAFPBLET WHEN
KILLED YOU SHED A TEAR, TY?
>> WHEN HE HIT THAT FLOATER IN
REGULATION.
[LAUGHTER]
>> MAN, IF I'D MADE, THAT THEY
WOULD HAVE SCORED, WE WOULD HAVE
LOST BUT WHEN I HUGGED MY MOM
AND DAD AND MY BROTHER, THEY
WERE TRI-CRYING SO I COULDN'T
HELP IT.
>> TY, WHAT A ROLLER COASTER
RIDE.
TALK ABOUT THE WHOLE TOURNAMENT
IN GENERAL AND JUST YOUR
MENTALITY GOING IN THESE
LAST-SECOND WINS ALL THE TIME.
>> JUST TO REMAIN FAITHFUL TO
THE LITTLE THINGS.
COACH BENNETT ALWAYS TALKS ABOUT
STAYING FAITHFUL AND HE TOLD US
DON'T GROW WEARY.
THAT'S A POSSESSION MINDSET, A
LIFE MINDSET.
JUST PLAY TILL THE BUZZER
SOUNDS.
THE FACT I MISSED THAT FLOATER
IN REGULATION AND COACH BENNETT
CALLED THE EXACT SAME PLAY SHOWS
HOW MUCH MY TEAMMATES BELIEVE IN
ME, HOW MUCH HE BELIEVES IN ME.
WE ALL BELIEVE IN EACH OTHER AND
IT'S THE MOST SPECIAL TEAM I'VE
EVER B
>> TY, YOU TALKED YESTERDAY
ABOUT HOW GROWING UP YOU WOULD
WATCH NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP
GAMES, STAYING UP LATE TO WATCH
THEM.
YOU MENTIONED THE MARIO CHALMERS
SHOT.
WHAT'S IT LIKE KNOWING KIDS
STAYED UP PAST THEIR BEDTIME TO
WATCH WHEN YOU GUYS JUST DID?
>> YEAH, IT'S UNREAL.
I HAVEN'T HAD TIME TO REFLECT ON
ANYTHING.
IT STILL DON'T FEEL REAL.
STILL DOESN'T FEEL REAL.
COME ON, BR ORGANIZATION, TALK
PROPERLY.
>> THIS IS FOR CAME.
THE QUESTION WAS KIND OF ASKED
BEFORE BUT HOW MANY DID LAST
WEEKEND'S GAMES HELP PREPARE YOU
BUYS FOR A STRETCH RUN LIKE THIS
AND PARTICULARLY -- PARTICULARLY
ALSO THE SEMIFINAL GAME?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I THINK WE'VE TAKEN EVERY
EXPERIENCE THAT WE'VE BEEN
THROUGH TOGETHER AND TRIED TO
USE IT IN A WAY THAT COULD  ■66
CHAMPIONSHIP.
YOU KNOW, A
AND ALL THE PRACTICES WHERE WE
PRACTICED LATE-GAME SITUATIONS,
WE TRIED EXECUTE AND WE WERE
VERY DISCIPLINED AND I THINK
THAT GOT US THROUGH A LOT OF
GAMES, ALONG WITH JUST TRYING TO
LEAVE IT ALL ON THE FLOOR AND I
THINK WE SUCCEEDED AT THOSE
THINGS.
>> THIS WILL BE THE FINAL
QUESTION FOR THE STUDENT
ATHLETES.
>> THIS IS FOR KYLE AND TY.
IT'S A LOCK HAUL TO A NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP FOR ANY TEAM,
PROBABLY A LITTLE BIT LONGER FOR
YOU GUYS.
CAN YOU IMAGINE GOING THROUGH
AND IT SURVIVING AND IT GETTING
TO THIS POINT WITHOUT -- WITH
ANY OTHER COACH OTHER THAN COACH
BENNETT?
>> TY, YOU CAN GO FIRST.
THEN KYLE, THEN DE'ANDRE.
>> UH, WHY WOULD IT BE LONGER
FOR US THANO'S, THOUGH?
>> PERHAPS BECAUSE YOU DON'T
WANT TO MENTION OR THINK ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED HOW LAST YEAR
ENDED.
>> OH, YEAH.
FOR US IT ACTUALLY WASN'T LIKE
THAT.
LAST YEAR IT DREW US EVEN CLOSER
TOGETHER AND IT MADE US ENJOY
EVERY PART OF THE SEASON EVEN
MORE AND MADE US ENJOY EACH
OTHER'S COMPANY ON THE ROAD.
WE GREW CLOSER OFF THE COURT.
SO IT WASN'T LIKE A RUSH TO GET
TO THIS CHAMPIONSHIP GAME AND
WIN IT SO WE COULD PROVE ALL YOU
GUYS WRONG.
WE JUST GREW MORE UNITTED AND
ENJOYED EVERY PART OF THE SEASON
AND OBVIOUSLY TO FINISH THE YEAR
LIKE THIS IS UNREAL AND TO
ANSWER YOUR QUESTION, NO, WE
COULDN'T HAVE DONE THIS WITH ANY
OTHER COACH.
>> TO EXPAND MORE ON THAT, COACH
SAID SOMETHING THAT REALLY
RESONATED WITH US IS RUN TO THE
START LINE, NOT THE FINISH LINE
AND WE'VE DONE THAT EVERY SINGLE
GAME THIS YEAR AND -- BUT TO BE
ABLE TO GIVE HIM A NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP AND DO IT FOR HIM,
THE PROGRAM AND OUR FAMILIES, IT
MEANS THE WORLD AND I WISH I HAD
THE WORDS BUT IT STILL DOES NOT
FEEL REAL.
>> DE'ANDRE?
>> YEAH!
JOY IS IN THE COMPETITION, LIKE
KYLE SAID.
IT WAS A GREAT WIN FOR OUR
PROGRAM, GREAT WIN FOR OUR
COACH.
WE'VE BEEN WORKING FOR THIS ALL
OFF-SEASON AND ALL THAT WORK
JUST PAID OFF.
ZUBIN: TECH HAS FIVE GUYS IN
DOUBLE FIGURES, VIRGINIA HAD
THREE.
THE THREE AT THE PODIUM.
THEY COMBINED TO SCORE 6 .
THEIR MOST IN THE GAME THIS
SEASON IN THE GAME THAT MATTERED
MOVEMENTS BACK TO THE COLLEGE
GAME DAY GUYS, RECE DAVIS.
RECE: THE VIRGINIA FANS ARE
ALREADY DEEP IN REVELRY AND
THEY'VE ALSO PICKED UP SOME
OTHERS ALONG THE WAY TO HELP
THEM OUT IN THEIR CELEBRATION
AND I'M TOLD IN CHARLOTTESVILLE
THEY'RE HAVING A GOOD TIME AND
THERE'S NAME CHANGE UNDER WAY
TO CHANGE THE NAME TO MR.
BENNETT'S UNIVERSITY.
THE PLAYERS COULDN'T QUITE
RECALL THE PLAY THAT WAS BEING
QUESTIONED.
THE DE'ANDRE HUNTER THREE FROM
THE CORNER.
WE REMEMBER EXACTLY HOW IT
HAPPENED.
JAY B.: IT  UPc'''■■■■ HIS SMAR
ABILITY TO HANDLE THE BALL AND
PEOPLE.
RIGHT NOW VIRGINIA BRINGING THE
BALL UP.
THROWN THREE WITH ABOUT 20
SECONDS TO GO!
JEROME WITH THE LEFT-HAND DRIVE
TO THE BASELINE.
HE DREW TWO DEFENDERS.
THIS W■■w■ssPEútt■ BY DE'ANDRE
HUNTER IN THE CORNER WHEN HE
KICKED IT OUT.
THAT'S A WIDE-OPEN THREE WHEN
THE ONLY THING IN THAT SITUATION
IS YOU CANNOT GIVE UP AS A
THREE.
BUT JEROME THROUGHOUT THE CORES
-- COURSE OF THE SEASON AND THIS
GAME.
HE WOULD KEEP HIS DRIBBLE AND
COME OUT THE OTHER SIDE.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN THAT HUNTER
WOULD HAVE GOT THAN SHOT BUT
THAT WAS ONE OF THE FUME
DEFENSIVE LAPSES THAT TEXAS TECH
HAD IN THIS GAME AND IN A WAY
COST THEM THE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP BUT IT SHOWS AND
YOU SHOWS EVERYBODY THAT
VIRGINIA DOESN'T LOSE THEIR
POISE AND THEY STAY IN
CHARACTER.
SETH: THAT PLAY, YOU THINK ABOUT
IT.
YOU SEE THE SCREEN BY BRAXTON
KEY.
TEXAS TECH CHANGED THAT.
AND ODIASE NEVER GOT A GOOD
ANGLE.
HERE COMES TWO DEFENDERS.
POOR KEUN COMMATION --
COMMUNICATION.
HUNTER IS WIDE OPEN, WOW, THEY
KNOCK DOWN THE THREE.
THERE IS A PLAY THEY'D LOOK BACK
AND SAY.
IF'D ASSY HAD PORSED HIM BACK,
CAN'T GET THE HELP.
GREAT POISE BY JEROME BUT JAY,
YOU SAID IT RIGHT.
ALL S?NG,■ AUBURN, PURDUE,
EVERY TIME IN THIS SITUATION
THEY REMAINED POISED.
CALM.
CALM IS CONTAGIOUS, THAT'S OUR
NEW SEASON.
JAY W.: ARE WE GOING TO MAKE
CALM IS CONTAGIOUS APUBLICABLE
IN YOUR LIFE?
SETH: NO, CALM IS CHAOS FOR ME.
[LAUGHTER]
JAY W.: ONE OF THE REPORTERS
ASKED TY JEROME, HOW DO YOU PUT
THIS INTO WORDS AND HE SAID I
CAN'T CO-THAT I DON'T KNOW THAT
THEY'LL EVER BE ABLE TO CARRY --
PUT THAT INTO WORDS -- INTO
WORDS.
IT'S A FEELING YOU'LL CARRY THE
REST OF YOUR LIVES.
WATCHING THEM BATTLE THROUGH
ADVERSITY AND STAY WITH IT.
THERE ARE A LOT OF TEAMS, SOME
PLAYERS WILL CHECK OUT.
THESE DUDES ALWAYS SEEMED LIKE
THEY BOUGHT IN AND BELIEVED IN
EACH OTHER AND THEIR COACH AND I
THINK THAT RESONATE TONIGHT
COURT ONCE AGAIN TONIGHT THAT.
BELIEF AND THE PAST THREE
GAMES, THE WAY THEY'VE WON HAHN
INCREDIBLE.
IT'S ONE OF THE BEST STORIES IN
THE NCAA TOURNAMENT I'VE EVER
SEEN, EVER.
SETH: YOU DON'T GO 63-4 UNLESS
TE AND YOU REALLY BELIEVE
AND BUY INTO WHAT THE VISION
YOUR COACHES HAVE.
TONY BENNETT SET A VISION WHEN
HE ARRIVED AT VIRGINIA.
HE SAID YOU HAVE TO LEARN TO
LOSE BEFORE YOU LEARN TO WIN AND
MAYBE THAT APPLIED TO THE NCAA
TOURNAMENT.
YOU HAVE TO LEARN TO LOSE AND IT
MIGHT HAVE BEEN PAINFUL, THE
1-16, BEFORE YOU CAN L TO
WIN A NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP.
JAY B.: I DON'T KNOW IF LAST
YEAR'S LOSS TO UMBC REALLY
FACTORED THAT MUCH INTO THE
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP.
I THINK THAT WAS ONE OF THOSEa
THINGS LIKEa  A SPORTS
PSYCHOLOGISTERE IT
SUCH A HUGE HURDLE BUT I THINK
THE FACT THAT THEY'VE BEEN A
WINNING PROGRAM FOR IN LONG.
THE LAST TWO YEARS, THEY HARDLY
EVER LOSE AND LOOK, THEY HAD A
COUPLE MIRACLES THIS YEAR,
AGAINST PURDUE AND AUBURN.
THOSE WERE MIRACLE-TYPE FINISHES
BUT THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
WIN A NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP THE
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE THOSE CLOSE
GAMES BUT THE WAY THEY PERFORMED
GAME AFTER GAME AFTER GAME.
THESE GUYS ARE LEGIT ON BOTH
ENDS OF THE FLOOR AND THEY'RE
ATLANTAED.
RECE: THOSE THREE STARS.
DE'ANDRE HUNTER TURNED IN AS
GOOD AN INDIVIDUAL PERFORMANCE
H ENDS ADDS YOU'LL■ SEE.
JEROME HAD 26-6 IN THE NCAA
TOURNAMENT.
THE MOST SINCE DERRICK ROSE AND
CAME GUY, HE WAS JUST THE MOST
OUTSTANDING PLAYER OF THE FINAL
FOUR.
KENNY: IF THIS GAME DIDN'T WORK
OUT FOR YOU, THERE'S ALWAYS NEW
ALASKA.
FUTURE BETS, KENTUCKY AND
VIRGINIA, YOU 1.
DUKE AND MICHIGAN, 8-1.
TEXAS TECH GETTING NO RESPECT.
30-1.
THERE'S NO SHAME IN FINISH
SECOND IN THIS.
THEY TWICE CAME BACK FROM
DOUBLE-DIGIT DEFICITS AND IF NOT
FOR THE THREE BY DE'ANDRE
HUNTER, WE WOULD HAVE SPENT IN
WHOLE TIME CELEBRATING TEXAS
TECH.
ZUBIN: COMING UP AT THE TOP OF
THE HOUR, "SPOR"'S
CONTINUING COVERAGE OF THE
VIRGINIA CAVALIERS' FIRST
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP AND A
TITLE GAME FOR THE AGES ROLLS ON
WITH "SPORTSCENTER" FROM LOS
WITWE DON'T JUST MAKE CARS...
ANGELES AT 1:00 A.M. EASTE
WE MAKE TECHNOLOGY
THAT MOVES PEOPLE
♪
THIS IS THE 2019 NISSAN ROGUE
FEATURING TECH LIKE
PROPILOT ASSIST
IT HELPS KEEP YOU
CENTERED IN YOUR LANE
♪
AND IN CONTROL
THIS IS HOW NISSAN INTELLIGENT
MOBILITY IS REINVENTING DRIVING-
FOR EVERYONE.
NOW THE MOST EXCITING TECH YOU
OWN IS IN YOUR DRIVEWAY
(Ariana)
What is he DOING?
(Vince)
He better not be messing up
our taxes.
(Lisa)
At H&R Block, you have your own
screen so you can see your
credits, deductions and tax
tips!
(Vince)
We need that now.
(Tax Pro)
What?
(Lisa VO) ♪
Know as you go at
H&R Block.
See your credits, deductions
and tax tips.
Block has your back.
So I can buy from
Enterprise Car Sales and you'll
takerade
That's right!
Great!
Here you go...
Well, it does need
to be a vehicle.
But - I need this out of
my house.
(VO) With fair, transparent
value for every trade-in...
Enterprise makes it easy.
New lower price.
Wow. That's a lot
of asparagus.
Yeah, you said get
a bunch of asparagus.
Oh, you...
bunch.
I... thought you kinda...
♪
ZUBIN: MORE "SPORTSCENTER"
COMING YOUR WAY IN ONE MINUTE
FROM NOW.
BLUE JAYS-RED SOX.
HOME OPENER FOR BOSTON.
TUESDAY AT 2:00 P.M. EASTERN
HERE ON ESPN AND THE ASTROS
OUTLASTED THE YANKEES ON MONDAY
NIGHT.
WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS ON
TUESDAY NIGHT ON ESPN.
KENNY: I'M PRETTY SURE I HAVE
THIS AUTHORITY.
ALL CLASSES ARE CANCELED AT
VIRGINIA TOMORROW.
TAKE THE DAY OFF, KIDS, BUT ACT
RESPONSIBLY TONIGHT.
"SPORTSCENTER"