BACK FROM A HORRIFYING INJURY.
AND HE'S DOING THE BOX JUMP.
>> INCREDIBLE.
>> TRULY INCREDIBLE.
WASN'T SURE IF HE BE ABLE TO
WALK AGAIN.
>> WHAT INSPIRATION.
THAT'S THE BEST THING I'VE SEEN
THIS YEAR.
>> YES.
NO QUESTION.
IF YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT RYAN
SHAZIER, TREMENDOUS PERSON,
TREMENDOUS TEAMMATE.
THAT REALLY NOTWITHSTANDING,
JUST PULLING FOR HIS RECOVERY
AND HE CONTINUES TOf]■.f]■].f].■
ALLóO■■■I
■■■■;■3■;3/■7■■■■s/;■■■■w;Osíw÷
>> ALL RIGHT.
>>> WELCOME TO "THE JUMP"
PRESENTED BY MICHELIN WIPER
BLADES.
>>> TODAY'S OPENING TIP, ONE MR.
ALEX CARUSO■AAA■■p TRYING BUT CO
DO YOU THINK -- WHO IS THE
HARDEST PLAYER NK ON IN THE
LEAGUE?
>> I THINK RUDY IS THE HARDEST
PLAYENK ON IN THE LEAGUE
AT 7
HASN'T BEEN A■UY LIKE HIM IN A
LONG TIME.
>> THAT IS NOT A MOUNTAIN YOU
WANT TO CLI
WELCOME TO "THE JUMP."
I'M ■I■L5) NICHOLS LOOK SIDE
NBA CHAMP, FORMER COACH OF THE ■
YEAR BYRON SCOTT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR JOINING
US.
COMING UP, WE'RE GOING TO BE
TALKING ABOUT THE BUCKS BECOMING
THE ONLY TEAM IN THE NBA THIS
SEASON TO HIT THE 60-GAME WIN
MARK.
IS THAT SOMETHING, NOTHING, OR
EVERYTHING?
WE'LL DISCUSS IN A MOMENT.
BUT FIRST, VINCE LOMBARDI IS
CREDITED FOR SAYING WINNING
ISN'T EVERYTHING, IT'S THE ONLY
THING.
PERSONALLY, I WOULD BEG TO
DIFFER WITH THAT ON A NUMBER OF
LEVELS, BUT HERE'S WHAT I KNOW
FOR SURE.
VINCE LOMBARDI DIDN'T PLAY IN
THE NBA DURING THE GOLDEN STATE
ERA.
TO SAY THE WARRIORS HAVE BEEN
SMOTHERING IS AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
THEY HAVE WON THREE OF THE LAST
FOUR TITLES, CAN THROW OUT A
STARTING UNIT OF FIVE ALL-STARS,
PLUS FEATURE THE GREATEST
SHOOTER OF ALL TIME, AND THAT
WAS BEFORE HE GOT CONTACT
LENSES.
SO WHILE, YES, ABSOLUTELY THERE
ARE OTHER TEAMS THAT COULD MAYBE
POSSIBLY WIN THE TITLE THIS
YEAR, LET'S FACE IT.
THE WARRIORS ARE STILL THE
OVERWHELMING FAVORITE.
WHICH MEANS THAT IN A LEAGUE OF
NEARLY 500 PLAYERS,BUT 15
EM NEED TO RECONCILE
THEMSELVES THAT WINNING MAY NOT,
IN FACT, BE THE  T
MAYBE THAT IS WHY AS THIS NBA
LAST FINAL BREATH, WE ARE SEEING
SUCH A STRONG ATTEMPT TO
MANIPULATE THE PLAYOFF BRACKET
WITH THE IDEA, I GUESS, THAT IF
BEING THE LAST TEAM STANDING
DOESN'T SEEM TO BE A SUPER
LIKELY OPTION, YOU AT LEAST WANT
TO BE STANDING AS LONG AS
POSSIBLE.
AND WITH THAT, LET'S GO TO
PORTLAND, SHALL WE?
YOU'D THINK LAST NIGHT THE
NUGGETS WOULD BE TRYING TO BEAT
THLAZERS BECAUSE IT IS A
BASKETBALL GAME AFTER ALLTEAD,
PLAYER.
DENVER SAT JAMAL MURRAY.
DENVE PAUL M.HAT'S TWO-THIRDS O
STARTING LINEUP.
I GUESS THAT COULD BE FOR REST,
AS THE TEAM TALKED ABOUT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE TEAM'S
OTHER TWO REGULAR STARTERS, GAR.
BUT THEY WEREN'T ALLOWED TO PLAY
IN THE FOURTH QUARTER.
THE NUGGETS ACTUALLY HAD A
SEVEN-POINT LEAD IN THIS GAME
WITH 4:30 TO PLAY.
COACH MIKE MALONE STILL WOULDN'T
PUT HARRIS OR BARTON IN TO HELP
SEAL THE WIN.
AS A RESULT, THE NUGGETS  IN
FACT, COUGH UP THE E, WHICH I
TO SAY  LEAST SEEMS LIKE
IT WAS THE INTENTION.
WHY?
WELL, HERE ARE THE STANDINGS AS
OF TODAY.
THE ROCKETS, THEY'RE IN THIRD
RIGHT NOW.
BY PROPPING UP PORTLAND, DENVER
HOPES TO MOVE TO THREE, WHICH
WOULD KICK HOUSTON TO THE NUMBER
FOUR SPOT AND KEEP THE NUGGETS
FROM HAVING TO SEE HOUSTON IN
THE SECOND ROUND.
DENVER DID JUST LOSE TO THE
ROCK NEARLY 30 THE OTHER
DAY.
SO I CAN SEE WHY THE NUGGETS
WOULD BE FEELING A LITTLE SHELL
SHOCKED.
IT'S NOT A GOOD MATCFOR ■
■KY GAME DENVER
IS PLAYING
THE ROCKETS STILLOL THEIR
O STAY OUT O
SO YEAH, HOUSTON COULD DROP TO
NUMBER FOUR, BUT THANKS TO
DENVER, LET'S CALL IT, I DON'T
KNOW, LET'S SAY NOT REALLY GOING
FOR IT IN PORTLAND LAST NIGHT.
NOW HOUSTON ALSO HAS THE CHANCE
TO GRAB THE NUMBER TWO SEED IF
EVENTS THE NEXT COUPLE NIGHTS
FALL THEIR WAY, WHICH MEANS
DENVER COULD STILL HAVE THAT
UNFAVORABLE MATCHUP AND NOT HAVE
HOME COURT.
THAT ASSUMES DENVER GETHE
D RCE
NUGGETS DROP TO THREE, THEY'LL
BE FACING A HIGHER SEED IN THE
FIRST ROUND.
I GET IT.
THE NUGGETS DIDN'T MAKE THE
YOFFS LAST YEA
GETTING TO THE CON■■IT
STORY.
OF COURSE, I UNDERSTAND THE
INSTINCT TO TRY TO STACK THE
DECK IN FAVOR OF THAT.
THE PROBLEM IS WHILE WINNING MAY
NOT BE THE ONLY THING, IT IS
GENERALLY A GOOD THING IN PRO
SPORTS.
BY EFFECTIVELY TRYING TO LOSE
LAST NIGHT, THE NUGGETS ARE
TEMPTING THE BASKETBALL GODS,
SOMETHING EVEN VINCE LOMBARDI
WOULD TELL YOU IS DANGEROUS.
BYRON, THERE'S A LOT TO PLAY
FOR, SEEDINGWISE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
HOW MUCH ATTENTION DID YOU GIVE
IT AS A PLAYER, WHO YOU WERE
GOING TO PLAY AND HOW THE
BRACKET WOULD LOOK?
>> I GAVE IT A LOT OF ATTENTION
BECAUSE YOU KNOW AS A PLAYER,
YOU KNOW THE TEAMS YOU HAVE A
LOT OF SUCCESS AGAINST.
YOU KNOW THE TEAMS YOU STRUGGLE
AGAINST.
IF YOU KNOW YOU HAVE A CHANCE TO
MEET THEM IN THE PLAYOFFS, YOU
KNOW THAT YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE -- YOU KNOW, LIKE I SAID,
IF I STRUGGLED AGAINST THEM, I
KNEW IT WAS GOING TO BE A TOUGH
SERIES.
WE COULD HAVE STRUGGLED AGAINST
THEM AS A TEAM AS WELL.
I'M N TALKING ABOUT FROM
AN INDIVIDUAL STANDPOINT.
DENVEEASTING THEIR
FAIT RIGHT HERE.
THEY'RE MESSING WITH FIRE
BECAUSE AGAIN, IF HOUSTON GETS
UP TO THAT TWO SAND7AKES
HOME DVANC&■)
DENVER, MEETS THEM IN THE SECOND
ROUND, I DON'T■HINK DENVER CAN
BHEM IF THEY'RE THE HOME
I THINK THAT'S GOING TOWITH .■
TOUGH MATCHUP.
I DON'T THINK THEY WANT TO FACE
THEM IN THE SECOND ROUND.
THIS IS GOING TO BE -- I KNOW
THEY'RE HOPING THAT HOUSTON
DROPS TO THAT FOUR SPOT SO
HOUSTON HAS TO PLAY GOLDEN
STATE.
TO ME, YOU JUST TRY TO WIN EVERY
GAME RIGHT NOW WHEN YOU CAN TO
GET THAT MOMENTUM GOING INTO THE
PLAYOFFS.
>> I'M REMINDED OF THE 2006
CLIPPERS WHO DROPPED ALL THE WAY
TO THE SIXTH SO THEY COULD PLAY
DENVER AT THE THREE BACK IN THE
DAYS WHEN IF YOU WON YOUR
DIVISION, YOU WOULD
AUTOMATICALLY GET THERE.
THEY BEAT DENVER.
I'M NOT SURE THIS IS ENTIRELY
WHAT DENVER IS DOING.
>> NO, THEY CAME OUT AND SAID
ALL THE THINGS YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO SAY.
WE WANT TO GIVE OUR GUYS SOME
REST.
I DIDN'T PUT THOSE GUYS BACK IN
THE END OF THE GAME BECAUSE THE
BENCH GUYS WERE PLAYING SO WELL.
>> LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT MY
NIGHTMARE.
WATCHING MARCUS SMART BE TAKEN
BACK TO THE LOCKER ROOM IN A
MEANINGLESS GAME YESTERDAY
AGAINST ORLANDO.
MEANINGLESS AT LEAST FOR THE
CELTICS, NOT ORLANDO.
JASON TATUM, SHIN CONTUSION.
THERE WAS A MOMENT YESTERDAY
MORNING WHERE DANNY GREEN LOOKED
LIKE HE MIGHT HAVE TWEAKED AN
ANKLE LATE.
I WONDER IF PUTTING GUYS IN
BUBBLE WRAP -- WOULD YOU RATHER
HAVE YOUR HEALTH OR YOUR
SEEDING?
>> BYRON, YOU JUST SAID, HEY,
I'M NOT SURE THEY COULD BEAT
HOUSTON IN A POTENTIAL
SECOND-ROUND MATCHUP ANYWAY.
IF YOU THINK NO MATTER WHAT,
HOME COURT OR NOT, YOU'RE NOT
BEATING THAT TEAM, THERE'S
SOMETHING TO BE SAID FOR TRYING
TO PROP UP PORTLAND TO TRY TO
GET THEM IN THAT THIRD SEED TO
AT LEAST TRY TO PLAY THEM IN THE
SECOND ROUND IF EVERYTHING FALLS
THAT WAY AND PUSH HOUSTON TO
FOUR.
I THINK THE NUGGETS SHOULD AT
LEAST PRIORITIZE HOME COURT FOR
AS LONG AS THEY CAN FOR AS FAR
AS THEY CAN OVER WHO THEY'RE
GOING TO PLAY.
DENVER IS A REAL HOME COURT
ADVANTAGE.
NOT EVERY ARENA IN THIS LEAGUE
IS A TRUE HOME COURT ADVANTAGE.
DENVER IS, BUT MAYBE IF YOU
DON'T THINK IT MATTERS O■■■■■■
OR THE ■
YAY BLAZERS,->RR■RR■■■TO GET TH
UP THERE.
>> FOR DENVER IT MATTERS.
ALL SEASON LONG THEY'VE BEEN A
GREAT HOME TEAM.
KEVIN, TO YOUR POINT, BOSTON'S
GAME DIDN'T MATTER.
THEY PRETTY MUCH SOLIDIFIED
THAT.
THIS GAME MATTERED.
DENVER AND PORTLAND, THAT GAME
MATTERED.
JUST LIKE RACHEL IS TALKING
ABOUT, FOR DENVER ESPECIALLY,
THEY TRY TO KEEP THAT TWO SEED.
IT MATTERS.
FOR ME, YOU'RE TRYING TO KEEP
THAT POSITION, YOU TRY TO WIN
THESE GAMES NO MATTER WHAT WITH
YOU CAN'T THINK ABOUT WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN TOMORROW.
YOU CAN'T THINK ABOUT INJURIES
AND ALL THAT STUFF.
I GET THEY DO HAVE THEM, BUT AT
THIS PARTICULAR POINT, LET'S TRY
TO SECURE THAT TWO SPOT TO THE
BEST OF OUR ABILITY, LET'S PLAY
OUR GUYS, AND ?C■E■E■ITHEN, HEY
IT'S ALL SAID AND DONE, IF WE
HAVE THE TWO SPOT, GO FOR IT.
>> I HAVE NOT BUGGED MIKE
MALONE'S OFFICE.
I CAN ONLY TAKE ON FACE VALUE
WHAT HE SAID TO THE MEDIA, THAT
THEY WERE TRYING TO WIN THE
BASKETBALL GAME, BUT THEY ALSO
SAT THREE OF THEIR STARTING FIVE
AND THEN DIDN'T LET THE OTHER
TWO PLAY IN THE FOURTH QUARTER.m
SO YOU JUST MAKE YOUR OWN
CONCLUSIONS.
I WANT TO REVISIT THE END OF THE
REGULATION BETWEEN THAT
HEAT/RAPTORS GAME ON SUNDAY.
GAME TIED AT 103-103, TEN
SECONDS.
REFEREE ERIC LEWIS BLEW HIS
WHISTLE, SO THE HEó■■■■■■■■■■■■N
INTO POSITION.
WADE, AS YOU SAW, RAN BACK,
DIDN'T END UP GETTING THE BALL.
JAMES JOHNSON MISSES HIS
LAST-SECOND SHOT ATTEMPT.
ERIC SPOELSTRA HERE, GO AHEAD.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS GOING TO HAVE TO BE
EXPLAINED TO ME.
I WILL PROBABLY FOREVER HAVE TO
AGREE TO DISAGREE.
I DON'T KNOW.
ERIC■■■■ HAD US ALL CONFUSED.
HE BLEW THE WHISTLE.
DWYANE HAD ALREADY MADE HIS CUT.
THEN DEON STEPPED OUT  BOUNDS
AND HANDED HIM THE BALL.
YOU BLOW THE WHISTLE WHEN YOU
HAND THE BALL TO SOMEBODY WHEN
THEY'RE OUT OF BOUNDS, NOT
BEFORE IT.
I'M STILL FIXATED ON THAT AND A
COUPLE OTHER CALLS.
THESE 12:00 TIPS, THEY'RE NOT
EASY FOR ANYBODY.
GET SOME SLEEP.
GET SOME REST.
THESE THINGS■X; ; )  MATTER.
>>WOW.
I THINK THAT WAS A VEILED SHOT
AT OFFICIATING.
IF YOU'RE OUT PARTYING THE NIGHT
BEFORE, THIS IS A HUGE GAME FOR
THE HEAT TO LOSE, OBVIOUSLY.
THAT COULD END UP -- WE COULD
LOOK BACK ON THAT AND THAT COULD
BE IT FOR THEM IN TERMS OF THE
PLAYOFFS.
THEY'RE ONE GAME OUT OF THE
EIGHTH WITH TWO TO PLAY.
>> IT'S A SMALL BEEF.
YOU KNOW THIS.
THAT WHISTLE, THE FOUR, THREE,
TWO, ONE, IT TRIGGERS THE
CHOREOGRAPHY.
SO IF YOU MISS IT, AGAIN, HE'S
ALREADY MADE HIS CUT, THE BALL
WAS NOT IN THE INBOUNDER'S HAND.
AM I RIGHT THERE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THE ONE THING I WOULD ALWAYS
TELL OUR PLAYERS, YOU DON'T
MOVE -- AS YOU SEE WHEN HE TAKES
THE BALL OUT, WHEN SHE SLAPS THE
BALL.
YOU DON'T MOVE UNTIL HE SLAPS
THE BALL.
A LOT OF GUYS WANT TO SEE WHAT
YOU'RE RUNNING ANYWAY.
I USED TO ALWAYS TELL MY GUYS,
WHEN THE REFEREE GIVES YOU THE
BALL AND STAND STILL UNTIL YOU
SEE HIM SLAP IT.
ERIC IS ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
THAT WAS A BAD JUDGMENT ON THE
REFEREEART.
AGAIN, YOU BLOW THE WHISTLE AND
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE THE BALL
THEN GIVE IT TO HIM TWO SECONDS
LATER.
THAT THROWS EVERYTHING OFF AS
FAR AS MIAMI IS CONCERNED.
THAT WHOLE RHYTHM WAS THROWN
OFF.
wANADE TO GET THE BALL
BECAUSE HE'S GOING GET KAWHI
LEONARD.
THIS WAS GOING TO BE SOMETHING
SPECIAL.
>> ARGUABLY MAYBE HIS LAST EVER
FINAL POSSESSION, TIE GAME
INSIDE OF 15 SECONDS.
>> HE'S RIGHT.
REES, WE TALK ABOUT THE
PLAYERS ALL THE TIME WHEN THEY
GO TO SOUTH BEACH AND L.A.
>> IT WAS TORONTO.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
CH HAS A GREAT NIGHT LIFE ■■■■■.
>> REFEREES, ■■ TO GET
SLEEP TOO.
>>■■■■ OKAY.
BUT I DO AGREE WITH HIM.
I DO SEE IT.
I OF COURSE SEE THAT RAN EARLY,
BUT KIND OF LIKE THE NCAA GAME
THE NIGHT BEFORE, LOOK, IN THE
FINAL FOUR GAME, THE KID STILL
HAD TO MAKE FREE THROWS.THAT'S .
IN THIS GAME, THEY HAD A W
OVERTIME.
T THAT POINT, YOU WANT
ñ■ THAT ■@OUT.
>> I GET IT.
NOT EVERYBODY --  HOW MANY
HUMANS ARE OUT ON THAT FLOOR
BETWEEN THE TWO TEAMS AND THE
S AND THE ASSISTANT
COACHES AND THE REFS.
NOT EVERY SINGLE PERSON IS GOING
TO OPERATE LIKE A ROBOT AND HAVE
A PERFECT MOMENT EVERY MOMENT
THEY'RE OUT THERE.
BUT THEY LOST THE
ENTIRE BASKETBALL GAME.
>> IF I'M A COACH, AND ERIC I
THINK WOULD SAY THE SAME THING,
IF HE WAS STILL ABLE TO GET THE
BALL TO D. WADE, NO BIG DEAL.
HE NEVER TOUCHED THE BALL.
WE ALL KNOW THE PLAY WAS FOR D.
WADE TO HAVE HIS HAN
BALL TO BE A-ÑT■T■ToT■T■T
ONE.
HE NEVER GOT A  GET IT.
>> IT'S FRUSTRATING, AND THE
STAKES ARE HIGH.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
COMING UP, WE'LL DISCUSS HOW
LAST NIGHT THE ROCKETS BROKE
THEIR OWN RECORD FOR MOST THREES
IN A SINGLE GAME WITH 27 AGAINST
THE SUNS.
SHOOTING RECORDS FOOL'S■>■>COME?
WE'LL DISCUSS THAT.
BUT TIME FOR OUR DISTANT
REPLAY.
IT'S THIS 1998,■,■■C■■a■C■#■; F
SHAQ.
>>OH!
>> SEE, I WAS■8■8■>Aza;ccKv WOU
BE LIKE --
>> BIG COUNTRY, YEAH.
DIESEL WITH THE BEHIND THE BACK.
♪♪
■■■ ♪♪
■■ú ♪ Orange
Vanilla Coke ♪
♪ Yeah, you heard
that right! ♪
Don't do it.
Anthony Davis?
Choose Mobil 1
Synthetic instead.
It protects engines better
than conventional motor oil.
You know, you look
much taller on TV.
The camera adds six feet.
Get 250,000 miles
of protection.
Upgrade to Mobil 1.
WE DON'T JUST MAKE CARS...
WE MAKE TECHNOLOGY
THAT MOVES PEOPLE
♪
THIS IS THE 2019 NISSAN ROGUE
FEATURING TECH LIKE
PROPILOT ASSIST
IT HELPS KEEP YOU
CENTERED IN YOUR LANE
♪
AND IN CONTROL
THIS IS HOW NISSAN INTELLIGENT
MOBILITY IS REINVENTING DRIVING-
FOR EVERYONE.
NOW THE MOST EXCITING TECH YOU
OWN IS IN YOUR DRIVEWAY
After walking six miles at
an amusement park...
■ ■
Bill's back needed a
vacation from his vacation.
So he stepped on the
Dr. Scholl's kiosk.
It recommends our best
Custom Fit Orthotic
to relieve foot, knee, or
lower back pain.
So you can move more.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to move.
>>> THIS IS FOR "THE JUMP,"
RACHEL.
IT'S A MAKE OR MISS LEAGUE.
>> MAKE, MISS.
>> THANK YOU FOR YOUR
PARTICIPATION, STEVE KERR.
MAKE, ADJUSTMENTS.
OVERTIME IN TORONTO, GASOL■4■4d
BAD PASS, BUT HI REACHES BACK
TO GREEN IN THE CORNER.
NICE LITTLE TOUCH, RIGHT?
>> I LOVE THE TOUCH PASS.
YOU MAKE A BAD PASS INTO A GREAT
PASS.
A OPEN, NICE LOOK.
THAT'S Y.
>> THOSE HANDS.
>> LOVE IT.
GST MORNING.STUMPING FOR DANNY ■
>> I WAS.
SECOND TE■■
>> BOOM.
BIG FANS HERE.
MISS ORGANIZATION.
THE TANKING GRIZZLIES AND
MAVERICKS ENTERED HT
JUST A GAME APART   z
STANDINGS.
WHO WANTS IT LESS?
ALL HELL BROKE LOOSE DOWN THE
STRETCH.
THE MAVS HAD ABOUT TEN CRACKS AT
TYING BEFORE FINALLY SENDING IT
TO OT AND WINNING.
I'M LEANING FORWARD INTO THE
SCREEN BECAUSE IF YOU WATCH
THIS -- I REWATCHED THIS LIKE
SIX■X TIMES YESTERDAY.
THIS IS AN INSANE FINAL
SEQUENCE.
AGAIN, WHO WANTS IT LESS?
WHO REALLY WON THIS GAME, KEVIN?
>> THE BOSTON CELTICS BECAUSE
MEMPHIS IS GOING TO KEEP THEIR
PICK THIS SEASON.
IT'S GOING TO MAYBE CONVEY NEXT
YEAR WHEN IT HAS FEWER
PROTECTIONS.
THE CELTICS ARE PLEASED.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> LOOKED LIKE THEY WERE PLAYING
HARD THOUG■p
■pñ>WERE TRYING TO WIN, EVEN
THOUGH WE KNOW THEY WEREN'T.
>> MAKE, EINMENT.■INGS PLAYED T
ME OF THE YEAR LAST NIGHT.
WE GOT ONE MORE LOOKH■ AT THE
LITTY COMMITTEE.
DO WE HOPE THE LITTY COMMITTEE
EXTENDS INTO NEXT YEAR AND
BEYOND?
>> I HOPE SO.
THEY MAKE IT LOOK FUN.
THEY'RE HAVING A LOT OF FUN OVER
THERE.
THE GUYS SEEM TO BE ENJOYING.
BUT THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
HAVE A GOOD SEASON.
THIS YEAR MADE VAST
IMPROVEMENTS, DID REALLY WELL.
GOT TO GIVE THEM CREDIT.
YOU GOT THE FANS THAT'LL START
JUMPING IN.
I WANT TO SEE MORE OF THIS.
>> REMINISCENT OF THE GOOD SQUA■
>> OF COURSE, I'M  OUT
THE BROOKLYN LYNCH MOB.
BUT LITTY COMMITTEE IS THE BEST
NAME.
MISS, WATCH THIS HERE..■0
WHAT DOES ONE TEAMMATE OWE THE
MMATE?
A DINNER ON THE NEXT ROAD TRIP?
KICKED YOUR TEAMMATE THERE?
>> IF YOU KICKED HIM THERE, YOU
OWE HIM AT LEAST TWO DINNERS
BECAUSE THERE ARE -- WELL, YOU
OWE HIM AT LEAST TWO D
>> A SPORT UTILITY VEHICLE.
>> YOU OWE HIM TWO DINNERS, FOR
THE LEFT AND RIGHT.
I'M JUST SAYING.
>> A SPORT UTILITY VEHICLE?
>> DINNER ISEASY.
>> DINNER IS TOO SMALL.
>> YOU'RE NOT TALKING ABOUT THE
PLACES I'M GOING.
>> HE HAS A NICER DINNER IN
MIND.
ALL RIGHT.
WATCH THIS.
WE WERE GOING NUTS OVER THE
WEEKEND AMONG "THE JUMP"
PRODUCERS.
ONE BY ONE, THE ROCKETS'
ROTATIONAL PLAYERS LEFT THE
BENCH WHILE THE GAME IS GOING.
THE GAME IS STILL GOING ON.
LOOK AT THE ROCKETS' BENCH.
>> THEY HAVE NOBODY THERE BUT
COACHES.
>> AND SHUMPERT.
>> BRINGING IT FOR HIS FORMER
TEAM.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE
THIS?
SO STRANGE.
>> I MEAN, THE 10:00 RESERVATION
APPARENTLY AT ONE OF BYRON'S
PLACES.
>> IT'S SO DIS THOUGH.
THAT IS SO DI■/.
I WOULD BE SO PISSED OFF IF I
WAS THE OTHER TEAM AND THE
PLAYE[ THE COACHES, THE ■yyyyyyW
■■W■W SEASON A■W■W■W■W■Wy■W■W;■.
>> NOT EVEN THE PLAYERS■
>> SO BAD.■■
WE HAVE HAD -- ■■■[IILIKE, THER
E■÷=■■■■■■■;■;■;■;■;■;■;■;■;■;■
SERIES ON■7■4WHEREn&y)y/n&■/y  G
ON THE BENCH, DID RAJON RONDO
THAT IS SO MUCH BETTER AMMATES
TH■/
THIS IS SO MUCH WORSE.
COME ON.
>>THAT'S TERRIBévév
>> COME ON.
UGLY.
LET'S STAY IN HOUSTON WHERE THE
ROCKETS BROKE THEIR OWN RECORD
FOR MOST THREES IN A SINGLE
GAME.
THEY WENT 27 FOR 57 BEHIND THE
ARC.
THIS IS LAST NIGHT OVER THE
SUNS.
ERIC GORDON LEADING THE WAY.
HARDEN HAD FIVE.
THIS SEASON, THE HOUSTON ROCKETS
HAVE HIT 1,305 THREES, ALSO AN
NBA REPORT.
SO LOOK, IT'S ALL WELL AND GOOD,
BYRON.
IT'S THE REGULAR SEASON.
THEIR NAME IS VERY PRETTY IN THE
TOP THREE SPOTS THERE.
IS THIS FOOL'S GOLD COME PLAYOFF
TIME FOR HOUSTON?
WE ALL REMEMBER GAME SEVEN OF
THE WESTERN CONFERENCE■/ FINALS.
THE SHOT SHEET THAT WOULDN'T
DIE,GHT?
IT WAS LIKE 27 IN A ROW.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, THIS ■ THEIR
STYLE.
THIS IS HOW THEY BEEN PLAYING
FOR THE LAST FOUR OR FIo/
WE'VE ALL SAID THATç■RE GOING
TO LIVE BY THE THREE, DIE BY THE
THREE.
I REMEMBER FIVE TO TEN YEARS AGO
YOU SAID YOU WOULD NEVER WIN
WITH THIS BRAND OF BASKETBALL IT
IT WAS ALWAYS FROM THE
INSIDE-OUT, THREE-POINT SHOOTING
WHERE YOU'RE AVERAGING, YOU
KNOW, 30, 40 THREE-POINTERS A
GAME.
YOU'LL NEVER WIN A CHAMPIONSHIP.
THEN GOLDEN STATE DISMISSED
THAT.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, WE SHOULD PUT
A CLOCK ON THIS.
HOW LONG IT TAKES TO GET ALL THE
Xs TO FILL IN.
>> AFTER ABOUT TEN STRAIGHT,
SOMEBODY'S GOT TO DRIVE TO THE
BASKET.
AT LEAST ONCE OR TWICE.
AGAI ■2ÑáÑáóá■LE.
THIS IS THE WAY THEY
THIS IS]HE]]]■]42]]■
CONTINUE TO PLAY.
>> I MEAN, I DON'T THINK IT'S
FOOL'S GOLD.
I THINK IT'S GOLD.
DID YOU NOTICE SOMETHING ABOUT
ALL THOSE TEAMS ON THAT LIST?
THEY'RE ALL REALLY GOOD.
THE GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS HAVE
WON, WHAT, THREE CHAMPIONSHIPS
IN FOUR YEARS.
CLEVELAND WAS SHOOTING THE BALL
EXTREMELY WELL THAT SEASON.
I THINK THIS IS JUST THE NEW
REALITY.
FOR DECADES, TEAMS WOULD GET
COLD, RIGHT.
NOBODY EVER SAID LIVE BYTH
TWO, DIE BY T
BUT THAT'S WHAT THEY WERE
SHOOTING.
IF YOU'RE TAKING A CONTESTEDç■■
E-POINTER AND■ ■  CSOMEONE IEN B
SHOT, BY ALL MEANS.
>>O■ó ■  IF TREVOR IRIZA IS TAK
SHOT FOR THE ROCKETS, SOMETHING
HAS GONE WRONG.
>> I JUST THINK THAT -- I THINK
IT'S JUST YOU MEASURE A SHOT IN
A LARGER CONTEXT.
RIGHT NOW IF YOU LOOK AT THE
IN THREE-POINT ATTEMPTS, I THINK
ONLY TWO OR THREE ARE GOING TO
THE PLAYOFFS.
LOOK AT THE TOP TEN TEAM■■■■■■■
THINK EIGHT OR NINE OF THEM ARE
GOIN
>> OBVIO■X■ ■CO8■■■8BE<OOD.
1E IS SAYING, OH, MAN, IS IT
A BAD THIN
THREE-POINT R
WAY, MAN.
IT'S FUN, IT'S GREAT.
IT'S A FUN THING TO BE GOING
INTO THE PLAYOFFS FEELING HOT.
IT'S JUST HARD TO SAY AFTER
WATCHING WHAT HAPPENS AT THE
MOST CRITICAL JUNCTURE THAT
THEY'VE HAD IN QUITE SOME TIME,
THEIR CHANCE TO GO TO THE NBA
FINALS.
THEY COULDN'T GET THAT THING
DONE.
SO THEREFORE, YOU HAVE TO
WONDER, OKAY, WHAT DOES IT MEAN
THEY'RE SETTING THESE RECORDS?
YOU WANT IT TO MEAN SOMETHING
LATER ALSO.
>> SURE.
MAYBE I THINK THE WARRIORS ARE A
TESTIMONY TO THE FACT THIS
BATTLE HAS BEEN WON.
NG DOWN, EVEN IF YOU LOSE o@
FOUR OR FIVE IN A ROW.
>> HAVE YOU BEEN TO LAS VEGAS
WITH CHARLES BARKLEY?
HE'LL TRY.
>>> COMING UP, THE BUCKS WON
THEIR 60th GAME OF THE SEASON
OVER THE WEEKEND.
THEY'LL BE THE ONLY TEAM TO HIT
THAT MARK THIS SEASON.
WE LOVE YOU, CHUCK.
IS IT SOMETHING, NOTHING, OR
EVERYTHING?
HANG TIGHT TO FIND OUT.
THE MAN'S FUN TO GAMBLE WITH.
With Advil, you'll ask...
What sore muscles? What
pounding head?
Advil is... Relief that's
fast. Strength that lasts.
YoWhll ask...■
With Advil.
(Ariana)
What is he DOING?
(Vince)
He better not be messing up
our taxes.
(Lisa)
At H&R Block, you have your own
screen so you can see your
credits, deductions and tax
tips!
(Vince)
We need that now.
(Tax Pro)
What?
(Lisa VO) ♪
Know as you go at
H&R Block.
See your credits, deductions
and tax tips.
Block has your back.
HEADER.
TWO OF THE BIGGESTd÷d÷d÷d÷■÷ GA
NIGHT WITH PLAYOFF IMPLICATIONS.
OUR COVERAGE BEGINS WITH "NBA
COUN■■tC■■ú0 EASTERN ON ESPN
AND THE ESPN APP.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
STILL HERE WITH BYRON SCOTT AND
KEVIN.
WE HAVE TO BRING BACK OUR
FAVORITE GAME.
SOMETHING, NOTHING, OR
EVERYTHING.
WITH A WIN OVER THE HAWKS LAST
NIGHT, THE BUCKS BECAME THE ONLY
TEAM TO REACH 60 WINS THIS
SEASON.
MILWAUKEE HASN'T WON 60 GAMES
SINCE THE '80, '81 SEASON.
BYRON, IS THIS SOMETHING,
NOTHING, OR EVERYTHING?
>> THIS IS EVERYTHING.
EVERYTHING.
FOR THIS TEAM TO BE ABLE TO
ACHIEVE THAT GOAL AND HAVE THE
BEST RECORD IN T NBA, WHICH
MEANS RIGHT NOW THEY ARE THE
BEST TEAM IN THE NBA, YOU GOT TO
GIVE THE MILWAUKEE BUCKS AND
COACH BUD A LOT OF CREDIT FOR
BEING ABLE TO ACCOMPLISH THIS
GOAL.
>> THIS IS A DOMINANT TEAM.
THIS IS A TOP OF■;■;■;■) A TOP .
THEY CAN BEAT YOU FAST.
THEY CAN BEAT YOU SLOW.
THEY CAN BEAT YOU BIG.
THEY CAN BEAT YOU SMALL.
THEY CAN BEAT YOU ON THE
OUTSIDE.
THEY CRUSH IT AT THE RIM.
OTECT THE RIM.w&
THEY DO EVERYTHING.■HINK THOSE T
RSATILE, THEY CAN MORPH
THEMSELVES INTO WHATEVER A
PLAYOFF SERIES, A PLAYOFF GAME,
TO ME, THA■@LLY DANGEROUS O■Ñ]<G
COME THE PLAYOFFS.
I  DON'T DO THIS LIGHTLY.
THEY ARE INKLINGS OF THE 4,
'15 WARRIORS IN TERMS OF STYLE,
IN TERMS OF COND IN TERMS OF
THE WAY THEY COMPORT THEMSELVES.
>> I AGREE WI THAT.
I AGREE WIWHAT WE■■■K
GIANNIS IS ABOUT TO BLOW UP
INTO, NOT TALKING ABOUT HOW HIGH
HE IS ALREADY, BUT MAYBE
STRATOSPHERE LEVEL.
I DON'T THINK YOU CAN SAY THE
BEST TEAM IN THE NBA.
THE WARRIORS ARE THE BEST TEAM
IN THE NBA.
>> I'M SAYING BY THEIR RECORD,
60 WINS, THEY'RE THE BEST TEAM.
>> YOU THINK IF THE WARRIORS
WEREN'T IN THE EAST, THEY
WOULDN'T HIT 60?
>> BUT THEY'RE NOT IN THE EAST.
THEY'RE THE BE GOING INTO
THE PLAYOFFS IN THE NBA.
>> THEY HAVE THE BEST BODY OF
WORK.
>> THEY HAVE THE BEST RECORD.
THAT'S THE BOTTOM LINE.
>> THE BROOKLYN NETS AND ORLANDO
MAGIC BOTH CLINCHED PLAYOFF
BERTHS YESTERDAY, SNAPPING
SIGNIFICANT DROUGHTS.
FOR THE NETS, THEIR FIRST
APPEARANCE SINCE 2015, WHILE THE
MAGIC HADN'T REACHED THE PLAYOFF
SINCE TRADING DWIGHT HOWARD IN
2012.
THAT'S CORRECT.
HAVE NOT REACHED THE PLAYOFFS
SINCE THEN.
>> WOW.
>> VERY EMOTIONAL LAST NIGHT, BY
THE WAY.
THE ENTIRE LOCKER ROOM.
WHO DO YOU THINK IS MORE
DANGEROUS COME PLAYOFF TIME, THE
NETS OR THE MAGIC?
>> I GIVE AN EDGE TO THE NETS,
AND THIS IS WHY.
THEY HAVE SO MUCH■@
■>■.
YOU'VE GOT USSELL.
LeVERT IS GNG HEALTHIER.
JOE HARRIS JUST DRAINS SHOTS,
AND THEY KNOW HOW TO FIND GOOD
LOOKS.
I THINK PERIMETER PTH, THEY
REALLY HUSTLE DEFENSIVELY AS
WELL.
>> YEAH, I AGREE WITH KEVIN
100%.
I THINK THEY'RE A LOT MORE
DANGEROUS THAN THE ORLANDO MAGIC
JUST BECAUSE OF WHAT HE SAID.
THEIR PERIMETER OFFENSE AND
DEFENSE HAS BEEN GREAT ALL
SEASON LONG.
THEY GOT AN ALL-STAR IN DeANGELO
RUSSELL.
YOU GOT JOE HARRIS WHO CAN KNOCK
DOWN THREES FROM EVERYWHERE.
AND THEY PROTECT THE RIM ON THE
DEFENSIVE END AS WELL AS ANYBODY
IN THE LEAGUE.
AND THE FACT THEY JUST SEEM TO
ENJOY PLAYING WITH ONE ANOTHER.
THEY SEEM TO HAVE A LOT OF FUN.
I REALLY THINK THAT THEY HAVE --
I MEAN, THEY'RE GOING TO BE THE
SIX SEED AS OF RIGHT NOW.
THEY'LL HAVE THEIR HANDS FULL
WITH PHILLY.
IT WILL BE AN INTERESTING
SERIES.
>> I WANT TO GIVE A QUICK
SHOUTOUT TO THE MAGIC.
I THINK THEY'VE JUST DONE
SOMETHING REA■ THIS YEAR.
OUB
>> THERE'S A LOT TO BE SAID FOR
IN THIS LEAGUE WE'RE GOING TO
PLAY A VERY CONVENTIONAL BUT
COMPETENT BRAND OF DEFENSE.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO TURN THE BALL
WE'RE GOING TO OWN THE DEFENSIVE
GLASS.
IF YOU CAN DO IN EASTERN
CONFERENCE, YOU CAN GET TO THE
PLAY THEY HAVE.
>> LET'HE GAMES WE'RE
SUPPOSED TO WIN, RIGHT?
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> IT'S SHOCKING HOW FAR AHEAD
THAT PUTS YOU.
I DO WANT TO CONGRATULATE BOTH
OF THOSBASES TOO.
THAT'S A LONG TIME TO SUFFER AN
YEARS, BUT IT WAS A HARD-FOUGHT
FEW YEARS.
GOOD FOR THEM ALL THE WAY
AROUND.
>>> I WANT TO ADDRESS THE PIECE
THAT KYLE KORVER WROTE FOR THE
PLAYERS TRIBUNE.
HE SHARES HIS OWN FEELS ON THE
INCIDENT WITH THE NYPD.
HE TALKS ABOUT HOW HIS REACTION
AT THE TIME IS NOT SOMETHING
HE'S REALLY PROUD OF NOW.
HE ALSO TALKS ABOUT HOW ALL THIS
WAS BROUGHT UP AFTER THE
INCIDENT BETWEEN RUSSELL
WESTBROOK AND THAT FAN IN UTAH
ON MARCH 11th.
IT'S ABOUT SO MUCH MORE THAN
THAT THOUGH BECAUSE HE ADDRESSES
THE ISSUE OF WHITE PRIVILEGE.
IN THE PIECE, KORVER ASKS THE
FOLLOWING QUESTIONS.
QUOTE, HOW CAN I, AS A WHITE
MAN, PART OF THIS SYSTEMIC
PROBLEM, BECOME PART OF THE
SOLUTION WHEN IT COMES TO RACISM
IN MY WORKPLACE, IN MY
COMMUNITY, IN THIS COUNTRY?
AS FOR THE WESTBROOK SITUATION,
KORVER WRITES, QUOTE, THIS
WASN'T ONLY ABOUT RUSS AND SOME
HECKLER.
IT WAS ABOUT MORE THAN THAT.
IT WAS ABOUT WHAT IT MEANS TO
JUST EXIST RIGHT NOW AS A PERSON
OF COLOR IN A MOSTLY WHITE
SPACE.
IT WAS ABOUT RACISM IN AMERICA.
KORVER ALSO NOTED THAT AS A
WHITE MAN, I HAVE TO HOLD MY
FELLOW WHITE MEN ACCOUNTABLE.
WE ALL HAVE TO HOLD EACH OTHER
ACCOUNTABLE.
I WOULD URGE EVERYONE OUT THERE
TO READ THE FULL PIECE.
KYLE KORVER DIDN'T HAVE TO
CO-WRITE THIS.
HE WENT OUT AND DID IT AND PUT
HIS NAME AND WANTED TO PUT THE
CONVERSATION OUT THERE.
NOT AMONG THE PEOPLE WHO ARE
FORCED TO HAVE IT EVERY DAY,
WHETHER THEY LIKE IT OR NOT, BUT
THE PEOPLE WHO MAYBE AREN'T
HAVING IT QUITE ENOUGH, HIM
TAKING THAT TIME TO REFLECT
ABOUT HOW HE CAN BE MORE OF AN
AGENT FOR CHANGE.
BYRON, WHAT DID YOU THINK UPON
READING AND HEARING ABOUT THIS?
>> FIRST TIME I HEARD IT, I SAID
PREACH.
KYLE, PREACH TO THE PEOPLE.
WE DO TRY TO SWEEP THIS UNDER
THE RUG.
IT'S SO DIFFERENT WHEN A BLACK
GUY SAYS OR A PERSON OF COLOR
SAYS THERE'S SO MUCH RACISM IN
THE WORLD.
I GOT PASSED OVER BECAUSE OF THE
COLOR OF MY SKIN FOR A
PROMOTION.
I DIDN'T GET THIS PARTICULAR JOB
BECAUSE OF THE COLOR OF MY SKIN.
SO I THOUGHT WHAT HE SAID WAS
RIVETING.
I THOUGHT IT WAS MIND BLOWING AT
CERTAIN TIMES.
I ALSO THOUGHT IT WAS VERY
EDUCATIONAL.
NOW YOU HAVE ONE OF YOUR OWN,
AND I'M TALKING ABOUT THE
PEOPLE, THE CAUCASIAN PEOPLE IN
SOCIETY, YOU HAVE ONE OF YOUR
OWN STANDING UP AND TELLING YOU
THAT IN THE WORKPLACE HE SEES
THIS ON A DAY-TO-DAY BASIS AND
HE WANTS TO BE ONE OF THE GUYS
OUT FRONT RECOGNIZING THAT IT'S
NOT FAIR ON ALL LEVELS AND THAT
PEOPLE OF COLOR DO GET TREATED
DIFFERENTLY.
HE DOES FEEL PRIVILEGED AT
TIMES.
I THINK IT WAS GREAT THAT HE
JUST BROUGHT THIS TO OUR
ATTENTION.
AGAIN, I WANT TO APPLAUD HIM
BECAUSE IF YOU READ THE PIECE,
IT IS REALLY RIVETING.
>> THERE WAS A REALLY
INTERESTING PORTION AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE PIECE WHERE HE
SAYS, LOOK, IN A LEAGUE THAT'S
75% PEOPLE OF COLOR, I AM A VERY
RECOGNIZABLE WHITE NAME.
SO IT PRESENTS VERY INTERESTING
UNDERTONES.
■vv■ ■88■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■1■■1■1
REASONS, POSSIBLY FOR THE WRONG
REASONS.
JUST KNOW IF YOU DO BUY M(■&0s■Q
JERSEY, IF I'M A SYMBOL, KNOW
THIS IS WHAT I BELIEVE.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS AN
INTERESTING COMMENTARY.
>> AND LOOK, PART OF IT IS
UNDERSTANDING, OH, AS YOU SAY,
BYRON, THIS PERSON MIGHT BE
DISCRIMINATED AGAINST BECAUSE OF
WHAT THEY LOOK LIKE, BUT ALSO
UNDERSTANDING IF YOU ARE SOMEONE
WHO'S BEEN GIVEN ALL THE
AUTOMATIC ADVANTAGES AT BIRTH
THAT YOU GET FROM BEING WHITE IN
THIS COUNTRY RIGHT NOW AT THIS
TIME, YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND HOW
FAR THAT PUTS YOU AHEAD OF OTHER
PEOPLE BEFORE ANYONE DOES
ANYTHING.
ANYTHING YOU EARNED OR DIDN'T
EARN, THAT YOU ARE STARTING FROM
SO FAR AHEAD.
HAVING KYLE COME OUT AND SAY
THAT, AS YOU SAY, SOMEONE THAT
MAY BE, AS PUT IT IN THE
PIECE -- HE GOES, WHEN I LOOK
AROUND AN NBA GAME, I LOOK MORE
LIKE A LOT OF THE FANS THAN I DO
LIKE THE PLAYERS.
AND I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT I
SEE THIS.
I THINK THAT'S WHY YOU SAW THE
TWEETS FROM SOME OF THE OTHER
PLAYERS.
I THINK THAT'S PART OF WHAT WAS
SO MOVING TOO.
IT'S THEM SAYING, OH, YOU
RECOGNIZE THIS.
YOU SEE WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, I'VE BEEN A
BIG KYLE KORVER FAN FOR A LONG
TIME.
OBVIOUSLY IT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH THE COLOR OF HIS SKIN.
IT'S THE WAY HE PLAYS THE GAME,
THE WAY HE'S ABLE TO COME OFF
SCREENS AND SHOOT THE BALL.
HE'S WORKED HIS WAY UP INTO A
12, 13, 14-YEAR NBA CAREER
BECAUSE OF HIS WORK ETHIC AND
THE WAY HE GOES OUT AND DOES HIS
BUSINESS EVERY DAY, EVERY SINGLE
DAY.
I'M A MUCH BIGGER FAN OF KYLE
KORVER OF WHAT I READ
TODAY.
>> AND HE DID TALK ABOUT THAT
INCIDENT WITH THE NEW YORK
POLICE OUTSIDE OF THAT
NIGHTCLUB.
HE SAYS, HE WAS MY TEAMMATE, WE
WERE CLOSE.
HE WASN'T JUST SOMEONE ON MY
TEAM.
WE WERE FRIENDS.
HE SAID, MY FIRST THOUGHT WHEN I
SAW THE NEWS REPORT THE NEXT DAY
IS, WHAT'S HE DOING OUT AT THAT
CLUB?
IT WASN'T, OH, WAIT, HE GOT
ATTACKED BY THE POLICE.
IF YOU REMEMBER, HE WAS INJURED
IN THAT EXCHANGE.
IT COST HIM THE REST OF HIS
SEASON.
LATER HE WON A CIVIL CASE
AGAINST THE NEW YORK POLICE.
IT WAS FALSE ARREST.
THEY DID NOT HAVE ANY RIGHT TO
PUT THEIR HANDS ON HIM THE WAY
THEY DID.
AND KYLE SAID THAT NOW THINKING
ABOUT IT, HE WOULD SAY, OH, IF
IT WAS ME, I NEVER WOULD HAVE
BEEN ARRESTED.
HE WAS WALKING OUT OF A CLUB AS
WHITE DUDE KYLE KORVER THAT TIME
OF NIGHT, HE BELIEVES EVEN IF HE
HAD GOTTEN INTO SOME SORT OF
EXCHANGE, HE WOULD NOT HAVE GOT
INTO THAT KIND OF PHYSICAL
ALTERCATION AND BEEN ARRESTED BY
THE POLICE.
REALIZING THAT, HE SAID, WAS
PART OF WHAT REALLY SORT OF
MOVED HIM, ESPECIALLY AS THIS
INCIDENT IN UTAH HAPPENED.
>> I COVERED THAT HAWKS TEAM.
IT WAS VERY INTERESTING,
TIME, THE KIND ONVEONS GO■ ■ E
ORGANIZATION.
IT WAS A REALLY CRYSTALLIZING
POINT NOT ONLY FOR THAT
FRANCHISE, WHICH ENDURED ALL
KINDS OF INDIGNITIES, COMMENTS
MADE BY PREVIOUS OWNER BRUCE
LEVINSON, BUT ALSO THE
CONVERSATION PROPELLED AT THAT
MOMENT INSIDE THE ORGANN.
IT WAS INTERESTING.
>> GO READ THE PIECE.
EXCELLENT WORK BY "THE PLAYERS'
TRIBUNE" AND KYLE KORVER.
HERE'S WHAT "THE JUMP"
RECOMMENDS TODAY.
ON THE ESPN APP, THE EIGHTH
ANNUAL LUKE WALTON ALL-STARS
COLUMN.
SO GOOD EVERY YEAR.
GUYS WHO FLOURISH IN NEW ROLES
AFTER BOUNCING AROUND A BIT.
ONE OF THE PICKS IS JOAKIM NOAH
WHO SAYS I'M MORE PROUD OF THIS
YEAR THAN WHEN I WAS AN
ALL-STAR.
PRETTY COOL.
CHECK IT■■■ ■ ■%■■■■■ >
Don't do it.
Anthony Davis?
Choose Mobil 1
Synthetic instead.
It protects engines better
than conventional motor oil.
You know, you look
much taller on TV.
The camera adds six feet.
Get 250,000 miles
of protection.
Upgrade to Mobil 1.
♪
(VO)
I know what you're thinking.
Electric, it's not for you.
And, you're probably right.
Electric just doesn't
have enough range.
It will neverive the wint.
Charging stations?
Good luck finding one of those.
So, maybe an electric car
isn't for you after all.
Or, is it?
♪
After walking six miles at
an amusement park...
Bill's back needed a
vacation from his vacation.
So he stepped on the
Dr. Scholl's kiosk.
It recommends our best
Custom Fit Orthotic
to relieve foot, knee, or
lower back pain.
So you can move more.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to move.
Sometimes, all you have
to do is read the signs.
Miller Lite has more taste,
fewer calories, and half
the carbs of Bud Light.
What are you holding?
Miller Lite. Hold True.
>>> TONIGHT ON SPORTSCENTER,
COLLEGE GAME DAY'S MUST-SEE
MATCHUP IN TONIGHT'S NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
UCH ARE COWBOYS
EXPECTING TO PAY DAK PRESCOTT IN
A NEW CONTRACT?
AND A LOOK AT THE EVOLUTION OF
TIGER AT AUGUSTA.
"SPORTSCENTER" RIGHT AFTER
"PTI."
♪♪
>>> AND THIS 47 OPEN CALIFORNIA
BANNER WILL BE MOVED AND HUNG
CHASE CENTER NEXT YEAR.
IT'S GOING TO HANG HERE
THROUGHOUT THE PLAYOFF RUN THEN
GO TO THE NEW BUILDING AT CHASE
CENTER TO HONOR THE 47 SEASONS
WE SAW WARRIOR BASKETBALL IN THE
OLDEST AND ONE OF THE GREATEST
NBA ARENAS WE'VE HAD THE
PRIVILEGE TO WATCH GAMES IN.
>> KLAY THOMPSON POSTING THIS ON
INSTAGRAM AFTER THAT GREAT
MOMENT.
SITTING UP HERE SOAKING IT ALL
IN.
I'M GOING TO MISS ORACLE, BUT
WHAT I'LL MISS -- LOOK AT KLAY.
HE'S THAT LITTLE DOT UP THERE.
WHAT I'M GOING TO MISS MOST IS
THAT OAKLAND LOVE BECAUSE
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE IT.
NICE MOMENTOR KLAY AFTER■h■8
HAVING A LITTLE MISSTEP WITH THR
MON
IS WAS A NICE GIVE BACK THERE.
BYRON, HOW WILL YOU REMEMBER
ORACLE?
>> I'M GOING TO REMEMBER IT IN
THREE PHASES.
I■■■@ME.
THE FIRST ONE IS AS A PLAYER.
WE PLAYED AGAINST THE GOLDEN
STATE WARRIORS WHEN THEY WERE
KNOWN AS RUN EY CAME INTO L.A.,
THEM IN A SERIES AND BEAT US IN
GAME TWO TO MAKE THE SERIES TIED
UP AT ONE API
THEN WE GO TO ORACLE, AND THEY
HAD THE ORIGINAL RUN DMC OUT
THERE PERFORMI INTRODUCINEM, WH
OFF.
WE END UP WINNING THE NEXT THREE
GAMES TO CLOSE THAT SERIES OUT.
>> WHY DID THAT UPSET YOU SO
MUCH?
>> YOU DON'T PARTY ON US, BACK
IN THE DAY.
YOU COULD NOT COME OUT AND PARTY
ON US LIKE THAT BACK IN THE DAY.
GOLDEN STATEME AGAINST THE  THAT
CLEVELAND CAVALIERS WHERE LeBRON
IN EVER■■z THAT COU■÷C=C=OSSIBL.
TCK HE HIT, THENKYRIE ONE
ON ONE WITH STEPH TO HIT THE
GAME WINNER.
ONE OF THE CLASSIC GAME SEVENS
THAT I'VE SEEN IN A LONG TIME.
IT HAPPENED IN ORACLE.
THEN THE THIRD THING IS JUST THE
ORACLE FANS.
T TEN YEARS, THEY'VE
BEEN SOME OF THE BEST FANS IN
NBA.
THEY'VE BEEN GREAT, VERY
SUPPORTIVE GROUP OF PEOPLE, VERY
KNOWLEDGEABLE ABOUT THE GAME OF
BASKETBALL.
THOSE THREE THINGS ARE MY TAKE
FROM ORACLE ARENA.
I W■■SS SEEING THOSE GAMES
PLAYED UP THERE.
>> I'M GOING TO REALLY MISS THE
NBA BEING IN THE EAST BAY.
I'M GOING TO MISS WARRIORS FANS
WHO I'VE ALWAYS$LOVED.
THE BUILDING A
@■[ TO CONCRETE AND NOISE
NARROW■>IDORS AND
ITS HANDSY SECURITY.
CAN WE STOPOMANTICIZING THIS
STRUCTURE?
I MEAN, ILOVE  I TRULY AM
ñg T■BAY.
I LOVE THESE FANS.
IT IS A TERRIBLE BUILDING AND
SHOULD BE IMPLODED AS SOON AS
POSSIBLE.
AND THAT EXPANSIVE AWFUL TAR
PARKING LOT, YOU NEED A TETANUS
SHOT TO GO OUT THERE.
IT IS AWFUL.
>> HANDSY SECURITY?
THAT'S A WHOLE OTHER SHOW TOO.
>> HANDSY SECURITY, I LIKET.
>> BUT I'M GOING TO MISS
OAKLAND.
>> TO ME, I THINK THE FACT THEY
CAME OUT FOR LAST NIGHT'S GAME
IN THE UNIS, THOSE ARE THE
THROWBACKS TO THE WE BELIEVE
WARRIORS TEAM.
FUNNY BECAUSE AT THE TIME THOSE
WERE NOT VERY POPULAR UNIFORMS
WITH THE FANS.
BUT OF COURSE THEY'VE COME TO
SYMBOLIZE THIS MOMENT.
I THINK IT'S INTERESTING THAT OF
ALL THE DIFFERENT ERAS OF ORACLE
WARRIORS BASKETBALL THEY COULD
HAVE PICKED, THEY PICK THAT.
TO ME, THE FACT THAT'S STILL THE
MOST SORT OF DEEPLY FELT
EMOTIONAL MOMENT FOR THE FAN
BASE, EVEN THOUGH THEY'VE WON
THREE TITLES --
>> THERE'S NOTHING LIKE IT.
>> IT SPEAKS TO WHAT THE FANS OF
ORACLE ABOUT.
THERE ARE SOME GOLDEN STATE FANS
THAT GET CRITICIZED FOR BEING
FRONT RUNNERS OR BANDWAGON
JUMPERS, OR, OH, YOU JUST WOKE
UP AND STARTED TO LIKE THIS TEAM
BECAUSE THEY WON TITLES.
THE TEAM THEY CAME OUT AND CHOSE
TO REPRESENT LAST NIGHT FOR
THEIR LAST GAME IN ORACLE WASN'T
A BANDWAGON JUMPING KIND OF
TEAM.
IT WAS THE TEAM THAT DID THAT.
IT WAS■í■í■í■í■í■í■í■í■í■í ALL
THEyND GRITTINESS AND
REPED SORT OF THE UNDER
NATURE OF OAKLAND TO BEGIN WITH.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS VERY FITTING
THAT THEY PICKED THAT TEAM TO
SORT OF BE LIKE, THIS IS OUR
FINAL STAND.
THEY DIDN'T WANT TO MAYBE
EMPHASIZE, OH, ?E■■■■E■■■■E■■■Eç
THEY WERE LIKE, THAT'S WIS
ALWAYSNG TO BE
>>>'S■■■■■■■■■■■■T RY COO■E>■
RI■ESON.
■■■■?■■■■■■ THAT CAVS' EPIC
3-1 CO■ I016 FINALS.
DID YOU KNOW THE WARRIORS  A
3-1 LEAD?
DID TER COME UP?
YESTERDAY WHILE CALLING THE
CAVS' FIRST GAME, HE CRITICIZED
THE WARRIORS FOR PICKING UP K.D2
AFTER THAES.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> THEY'VE LITERALLY -- YOU
UNDERSTAND.
YOU GOT TO DO THAT TEN TIMES OUT
OF TEN.
BUT YOU■ KNOW, WHERE I COME FRO
IN THE PARK AND IN THE STREET,
IF YOU'RE PLAYING AND LOSE
SOMEBODY, THE FIRST WORDS ARE
RUN IT BACK, SAME TEAM.
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
RUN IT BACK.
>> RUN IT BACK.
>> THAT'S HOW WE GREW UP, RIGHT?
GETTING EXCITED OVER HERE.
RUN IT BACK, SAME TEAM.
YOU DON'T WANT TO CHANGE
ANYTHING.
WE FELT LIKE WE'RE THE BETTER
TEAM.
WE JUST DIDN'T PLAY WELL ENOUGH,
SO LET'S RUN IT BACK.
THEY DIDN'T DO THAT.
THEY WERE LIKE, WE NEED TO
RELOAD, GET OUR BIG BROTHER.
THANKS, GUYS.
>> K.D. LEFT A COMMENT ON AN
INSTAGRAM POST THAT HAD THAT
CLIP SAYING, QUOTE, EVERYBODY
WANT TO BE FROM THE STREETS
NOWADAYS.
JEFFERSON RESPONDED WITH A LONG
COMMENT THAT READ IN PART, MY
SINGLE MOM LEFT L.A. TRYING TO
MAKE SURE ONE OF HER THREE BOYS
DIDN'T GET SHOT UP ON THE SAME
CORNER MY DAD DID THIS YEAR.
THAT JUST HAPPENED EARLIER THIS
YEAR.
OUR CONDOLENCES TO RICHARD'S
FAMILY.
I THINK WE CAN BOTH RELATE TO
SINGLE MOMS WITH THAT STRUGGLE.
WHAT IS YOUR REACTION TO THIS
EXCHANGE, KEVIN?
>> THAT PERCEPTIONS OF CLASS AND
AUTHENTICITY STILL HAVE REAL
CURRENCY AMONG PLAYERS IN THE
LEAGUE.
TO CLAIM STREET, TO MANY
PLAYERS, YOU NEED TO SHOW
STREET.
ALSO WHAT MY RESPONSE IS, DURANT
IS STILL IN THE BUSINESS OF
AND APPARENTLY THAT'S NOT GOING
TO CHANGE, EVEN ON TVE OF
THE PLAYOFFS.
HEY, THAT'S HIS WAY.
>> BYRON, YOU'RE FROM INGLEWOOD.
IF YOU WANT TO START PLAYING THE
STREET CREDIBILITY GAME, WHAT
DID YOU MAKE OF THIS?
>> I DON'T HAVE TO CLAIM THE
STREETS.
EVERYBODY KNOW WHERE I'M FROM.
SO WHERE CLAIM IT?
I DON'T HAVE TO CLAIM IT.
I'M WITH KEVIN.
IF I'M KEVIN DURANT, I WOULDN'T
HAVE EVEN COMMENTED ON IT, TO BE
HONEST WITH YOU.
HE'S A GROWN MAN.
HE HAD AN OPPORTUNITY.
THAT'S WHY THEY CALL FREE AGENCY
FREE AGENTS.
YOU GET A CHANCE TO DO WHAT YOU
WANT TO DO.
HE HAD A CHANCE TO GO TO A
DIFFERENT TEAM WHO HAD JUST BEAT
HIM IN THE PLAYOFFS BUT ALSO
MAKE THEM STRONGER BECAUSE THEY
JUST WON A CHAMPIONSHIP AND GO
AHEAD AND CHASE A RING.
THAT'S HIS PREROGATIVE.
I'M NOT THROWING SHADE AT KEVIN
OR ANYBODY ELSE WHO HAS A CHANCE
TO MAKE A DECISION BASED ON WHAT
THEY WANT TO DO WITH THEIR
LIVES.
THAT'S YOUR JOB.
THAT'S YOUR CHOICE.
I APPLAUD HIM FOR DOING THAT.
BUT I UNDERSTAND WHERE RICHARD
IS COMING FROM.
BACK IN THE DAY, HE'S RIGHT.
HE'S RIGHT.
BACK IN THE DAY WHEN WE ALL WERE
GROWING UP, YOU RUN IT BACK.
LET'S PLAY AGAIN.
>> BY THE WAY, HIS COMMENT
WASN'T EVEN REALLY DIRECTED AT
KEVIN DURANT.
HIS COMMENT WAS, HEY, WE HAD
THIS CRAZY COMEBACK, AND
WARRIORS FANS AND IN SOME WAYS
SOME OF THE WARRIORS PLAYERS
WITH THEIR COMMENTS OVER THE
NEXT FEW MONTHS MADE SORT OF THE
DISTINCTION THAT THEY GOT LUCKY
OR IT WAS DRAYMOND GREEN'S
SUSPENSION OR■■EY OR
ANY OF THE THINGS THAT HAPPENED
HIS POINT WAS, HEY, IF YOU
REALLY THINK THAT THIS WAS SOME
BIG FLUKE, WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU
JUST RUN IT BACK WITH THE SAME
TEAM AND SHOW SOME LOYALTY TO
YOUR GUY THAT YOU D AND ■■oAL■ ?
NOW, HE DID ALSO SAY IN THOSE
COMMENTS, TEN OUT OF TEN.
>> EXA
> BUT IT WAS NOT A SHOT AT K.D.
ANYWAY.
IF IT WANG A  IT WAS
AT THE WARRIORS.
>> THE ORGANIZATION, RIGHT.
>>> COME UP, WE'LL ABOUT A
POLL OF PLAYERS CONDUCTED BY TH.
THEY VOTED RUSSELL WESTBROOK AND
DRAYMOND GREEN AS THE MOST o■
RATED PLAYERS IN THE LEAGUE.
/Q'S /Q/Q/QLAYERS.
WE'/Q/Q■Q/Q/u■QREACT NEXT.
HERE'S OUR DISTANT REPLAY FROM
THIS DA■■y■■(&800■8■ ■8■ ■ YES,>
>> LONG REBOUND.
BEHIND THE BACK!y&■p
THAT HAS T THEIR FEET AT
MONTA E■8
>> JUST LOOKED LIKE STEPH
CURRY THE OTHER DAY TO KEVIN
DURANT.
LEFT HAND.
♪♪
■   ♪ Orange
Vanilla Coke ♪
♪ Yeah, you heard
that right! ♪
Don't do it.
Anthony Davis?
Choose Mobil 1
Synthetic instead.
It protects engines better
than conventional motor oil.
Uh, my oil works
just fine thank you.
Can it keep your engine
in excellent condition
for over 250,000 miles?
You know, you look
much taller on TV.
The camera adds six feet.
Seems like a thing people
would know. But I didn't.
Get 250,000 miles
of protection.
Upgrade to Mobil 1.
WE DON'T JUST MAKE CARS...
WE MAKE TECHNOLOGY
THAT MOVES PEOPLE
♪
THIS IS THE 2019 NISSAN ROGUE
FEATURING TECH LIKE
PROPILOT ASSIST
IT HELPS KEEP YOU
CENTERED IN YOUR LANE
♪
AND IN CONTROL
THIS IS HOW NISSAN INTELLIGENT
MOBILITY IS REINVENTING DRIVING-
FOR EVERYONE.
NOW THE MOST EXCITING TECH YOU
OWN IS IN YOUR DRIVEWAY
■■■■
Emerge Restored,
Replenished,
Fortified.
Emerge everyday with Emergen-C.
Packed with B vitamins,
Electrolytes, Antioxidants,
Plus more vitamin C than
10 oranges.
Why not feel this good
every day?
Emerge and See.
♪ There's something
out there ♪
♪ for you and me,  ♪
♪ And the American
road is calling, ♪
♪ so what's it
gonna be? ♪
♪ Hey it's an
amazing day, ♪
♪ Traveling our
own highway, ♪
♪ No here
it leads us ♪
♪ we can smile, ♪
♪ 'Cuz there's meaning
in the miles. ♪
♪  ♪
>>> HANGING OUT WITH PABLO.
WE'RE HERE IN A FNU TO
DISCUSS WHETHER AUBURN WAS
ROBBED.
>> IF THERE'S ANY TRUTH TO PAUL
PIERCE COM■■■■3■3■3■3■3■■■ CARE
D. WADE.
>> THE NBA PLAYER NOBODY WANTS
TO FIGHT.
>> AND PARKING LOT ■■■■■■■■■■■■.
BECAUSE THAT HAPPENED.
STAY TUNED.
>> WE'LL FIND OUT IF PAUL PIERCE
WANT TO FIGHT.
>>> THIS IS "THE JUMP" PRESENTED
BY MICHELIN WIPER BLADES.
>>> GOT TWO HUGE TITLE BOUTS ON
TAP FRIDAY NIGHT EXCLUSIVELY ON
ESPN PLUS, ENGLISH AND SPANISH.
START YOUR FREE TRIAL TODAY BY
DOWNLOADING THE ESPN APP RIGHT
NOW.
BUT I WANT TOHE NBA ■PLAYER POL
ALT
ATHLETIC.
122 PLAYERS WERE POLL■ú■ú■úzúTH
NAMES, BUT THEY DO HAVE TO GIVE
THEIR OPINIONS.
44.3% VOTED JAMES HARDEN AS
THEIR MVP THIS SEASON.THAT'S COV
FOR GIANNIS, 13% VOTING FOR
PG-13.
BYRON, DID YOU EXPECT MORE
PLAY VOTE FOR HARDEN?
EVERY SINGLE FORMER PLAYER WHO
HAS COME THROUGH THE SHOW SAID
I'M LEANING TOWARD GIANNIS.
CURRENT PLAYERS LEANING TOWARD
HARDEN.
>> I EXPECTED IT TO BE CLOSE.
I E■■■WIN IT.
WHAT HE WAS ABLE TO DO THIS
SEASON WAS REMARKABLE.
SOME OF THE RECORDS HE WAS ABLE
TO SET, SOME OF THE RECORDS HE
WAS ABLE TO CHASE WERE
RE.
I JUST THOUGHT IT WOULDN'T BE A
RUNAWAY.
GIANNIS HAS BEEN FANTASTIC ALL
SEASON LONG.
DWISE, BEST TEAM IN THE
LEAGUE.
I KNEW IT WOULD BE CLOSE, BUT I
GAVE THE EDGE TO JAMES HARDEN.
>> HARDEN WON THE PLAYERS' POLL
OVER STEPH IN ST FIRST MVP
YEAR.
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT HARDEN'S
GAME, THE WAY HE IS ON THE FLOOR
THAT PLAYERS LOVE.
>> IT WILL BE INTERESTING TO SEE
IF T GOES FOR THE VOTE FOR
MVP.
LET'S TALK ABOUT RUSS AND
DRAYMOND.
THEY WERE VOTED MOST OVERRATED
IN THE SAME POLL.
WHAT WAS YOUR REACTION TO THAT?
>> SO THIS I FOUND INTERESTING
FOR TWO REASONS.
FIRST, THEY ARE STATISTICALLY IN
TERMS OF PROFILE
DIFFERENT.
RUSS IS THE STAT STUFFER.
THEY HAVE ONE THING IN COMMON,
THEY'RE VERY ABRASIVE.
GIVEN THE OPPORTUNITY TO SUMMIT
AN ABRASIVE PERSON, YOU CALL
OVERRATED.I>> WHEN I SAW THIS,
RUSS' NAME, I SAID WHAT?
OVERRATED?
A MAN THAT HAD  STR■4q■>9■9■
SEASONS OF ■>E■E■E■TRIPLE-DOUBL
HAD ONLY BEEN DONE ONCE, BYspsp.
THIS IS ALL ABOUT HATE.
THIS IS ALL ABOUT -- YOU GOT A
BUNCH OF GUYS THAT JUST HATING
ON RUSSELL WESTBROOK'S GAME
BECAUSE THERE'S NO WAY IN HELL
THIS GUY IS OVERRATED.
MATTER OF FACT, HE'S UNDERRATED.
UNDERRATED.
>> I MEAN, LOOK, THIS IS WHY,
KEVIN, THE PLAYERS DON'T
ACTUALLY VOTE FOR THESE AWARDS
AT THE END OF THE SEASON.
BECAUSE YOU DO HAVE PERSONAL
BIASES REALLY COMING INTO PLAY,
GUYS WHO FEEL LIKE THEY HAVE TO
VOTE FOR THEIR TEAMMATES, GUYS
WHO VOTE AGAINST GUYS THEY'VE
HAD A DUST-UP OR GRUDGES
AGAINST.
WHEN WE SEE PLAYERS -- WHEN THEY
DO GET TO VOTE FOR THINGS LIKE
THE ALL-STAR GAME OR PLAYER
AWARDS, SOME OF THE VOTES ARE SO
OUT THERE.
THEY VOTE IN FELLOW PLAY WHO
BARELY PLAYED IN ANY GAMES.
IT GETS KIND OF CRAZY.
IT'S FUN TO SEE.
>> IF THEY COULD EVER INSTITUTE
A SITUATION WHERE MAYBE THE
PLAYERS CAN VOTE BUT THEY SHOULD
BE TRANSPARENT.
>> I LIKE THAT.
>> PLAYERS WOULD HAVE TO SAY WHO
THEY VOTED ■
I  THEN PLAYER VOTING WOULD
BE EVEN MORE o)■TER FROM
T -- IF P■E HTO NOT
ONLY VOTE BUT SHOW WHO
VOTEDFOR 4 NAME, DON'T YOU
THINK THAT PERSONAL FEELINGS,
GRUDGES, AND FRIENDSULD
COME IN SO MUCH MORE THAN
OBJECTIVELY WHO'S THE BEST
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> IF YOU WERE GIVEN A VOTE, YOU
WOULD JUST VOTE YOUR ENTIRE
LAKER TEAM.
>> YEAH, BUT I WOULD ALSO VOTE
IN MICHAEL JORDAN, OF COURSE AND
A BUNCH OF OTHER GUY
NK IF YOU MAKE IT
TRANSPARENT LIKE THAT, THEN IT'S
GOING TO BE REALLY■■■■■■■■■■■■■
GUYS THAT DON'T WANT TO TELL YO
MORE SAFER.