JON: WAY TO GO!
DAVID: WHAT WAS IMPRESSIVE, TOO,
BREGMAN OFF THE SWING OF THE
BAT, NO HESITATION, SCORE
EASY AND PHENOMENAL JOB BY BIRD
NOT PANICKING.
MAY HAVE HAD A PLAY AT FIRST
BASE.
BUT YOU COULD EASILY SEE HIM
D THE+/+/+/ASES.■#Z#■■■■■■■■■■■b
JON: A WALK, A DART AND A DOINK.
AND HERE WE ARE, 4-3.
GURRIEL.
DAVID: IT STARTS TO FEEL A LOT
LIKE THE SIGNATURE OF THIS
ASTROS TEAM WE'VE SEEN THE LAST
COUPLE OF YEARS, KEEPING IT
CLOSE.
THEY HAVE RELENTLESS AT-BATS.
THEY KNOW THEY'LL BE IN AT THE
END.
THEY'VE GOT A STRONG BULLPEN,
THEY PLAY GREAT DEFENSE.
IT CONTINUES TONIGHT.
JON: ASTROS TRAILED 1-0, 3-1.
THEY'VE COME ALL THE WAY BACK
AND LEAD IT 4-3.
THE ROOF IS OPEN, FOR ALEX
BREGMAN, A REALLY NICE ONE-OUT
PLATE APPEARANCE, ENDING UP
SCORING THE GO-AHEAD RUN.
1-2.
K-ZONE HAD IT CLIPPING THE TOP
EDGE OF THE STRIKE ZONE.
DAVID: TWO-SEAMERS REALLY COMING
BACK HARD.
YOU WANT TO NIT-PICK, JUST RIDE
THAT BALL A LITTLE BIT DEEPER,
GARY SANCHEZ, LET THAT THING GET
TO YOU A LITTLE BIT CLOSER --
MIGHT BE ABLE TO FOOL THAT
UMPIRE.
JON: AND A SWING AND A MISS AND
GURRIEL DOWN ON STRIKES.
A REMINDER, TOMORROW, THE RED
SOX HOME OPENER AT FENWAY PARK,
CHRIS SALE GETTING HIS START,
THE DEFENDING CHAMPS TAKING ON
THE BLUE JAYS AT 2:00 EASTERN.
AT 8:00 P.M., SHOW ME ME.
ASTROS ANDANKEES.
WE'LL BE BACK, ME AND ROSSI.
DAVID: GOOD, GOOD FRIENDS,■ ROSI
JON: OUR OTHER GOOD FRIEND, RICK
LIFFE WATCHING SOMEWHERE.
HERE'S MARISNICK NOW.
ASTROS LEAD IT 4-3, TWO OUTS
HERE IN THE EIGHTH.■
JUST OFF THE OUTSIDE EDGE.
REGARDLESS OF WHING
PLACE HERE TONIGHT, YOU STILL
GOT TO FIGURE THIS YANKEE
BULLPEN IS GOING TO BE ONE OF
THE BEST IN THE GAME THIS YEAR.
NASTY SLIDER.
DAVID: NICE CATCH THERE BY THE
FAN.
THEY DON'T EVEN HAVE BETANCES,
EITHER.
THEY HAVE SOME DEPTH DOWN THERE.
KIND OF A SIGNATURE FOR BRIAN
CASHMAN.
THERE HE IS.
BRIAN CASHMAN'S ALWAYS BUILT
THAT STRONG BULLPEN OF CLOSERS,
FORMER CLOSERS.
HARD THROWERS THEY'VE GOT DOWN
THERE, OVER AND OVER AGAIN, THEY
BRING GUYS THROUGH, 96-PLUS.
JON: BULLPEN TONIGHT OFFERING UP
TWO WALKS.
BOTH OF THEM SCORED.
FASTBALL MOVING ALL OVER THE,>;á
PLACE.
OTTAVINO WORKING HARD.
ONE OF THOSE SUBTLE THINGS.
MORE OFTEN THAN NOT YOU DENT --
DON'T LIKE TO USE YOUR GOOD GUYS
IN A LOSS.
SWING AND A MISS.
AND THAT IS THAT.
ROBERTO OSUNA COMING IN TO TRY
TO CLOSE IT OUT.
9-1-2 AND JUDGE
♪♪
When cravings hit, hit back.
Choose Glucerna, with
slow release carbs
to help manage blood sugar, and
start making everyday progress.
Glucerna.
Lowe's knows you
do laundry right.
We do it right too,
with select Whirlpool washers
with "Load & Go" dispensers
that go up to up to
40 loads between r■;
So you can pour it
and ignore it.
Get great deals on great gear.
Bring the kids
for our free Easter Event
with giveaways, crafts,
an egg hunt,
and a free picture
with the Easter Bunny.
Go online to learn more.
Your Adventure Starts Here
KENNY: COMING UP ON
"SPORTSCENTER," WE'RE INSIDE THE
YANKEES START TO THE SEASON.
WHAT THEY CAN DID TONIGHT THAT
HASN'T BEEN DONE IN 16 YEARS.
AND WE'LL BUM YOU OUT.
DETAILING THE WORST INDIVIDUAL
STARTS IN MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL.
JON: THANKS, KENNY.
"SPORTSCENTER" COMING UP.
WE GO TO THE NINTH AND ROBERTO
OSUNA ON THE RIGHT-HANDER,
TRYING TO PICK UP HIS THIRD
SAVE.
RIGHT FIELD, URSA ONE(■■C■C■gfE.
AGAIN, "SPORTSCENTER" IS NEXT.
DAVID: JUST A BUNCH OF
SUPERSTARS FLASHING ON THE
SCREEN.
HOW ABOUT THAT INFIELD?
JON: IT'S CRAZY.
DAVID: LIKES THAT FOUR-SEAMER UP
LA HE'S GOT A LITTLE
CUTTER-SLIDER, HE CAN MAKE IT
BIG SOMETIMES.
HE'LL CUT IT SOMETIMES.
HE'S GOT GREAT COMMAND WITH
THAT.
REALLY TOUGH FOR RIGHT-HANDED
HITTERS.
HE'LL HAVE HIS WORK CUT OUT FOR
HIM WITH AARON JUDGE ON DECK.
JON: THEY GOT OSUNA LAST YEAR
FROM THE BLUE JAYS JULY 30.
HE WAS IN THE MIDDLE OF A
SUSPENSION FOR VIOLATING MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL'S JOINT DOMESTIC
ABUSE, ASSAULT POLICY.
WITH THE ASTROS LAST YEAR.
ONCE HE WAS ACTIVE, HE PITCHED
WELL.
23 APPEARANCES, 22 2/3 INNINGS
AND .199 E.R.A.
GARDNER IN THE AIR.
CORREA CALLING EVERYBODY OFF.
TWO DOWN.
ONE-RUN GAME, IF YOU'RE A FAN,
THEN YOU'RE JUST INTERESTED.
YOU CAN'T REALLY HOPE FOR
ANYTHING ABOUT BETTER THAN THIS.
DAVID: NO.
WHAT A GREAT BALL GAME WE'VE
GOTTEN TONIGHT AND IT COMES DOWN
TO ONE OF PREMIER HOME RUN
HITTERS IN THE GAME VERSUS THE
ASTROS CSUNA.
WE PAID THE PRICE OF ADMISSION
FOR.
JON: ROCKET TO RIGHT FIELD,
RIGHT AT SPRINGER.
BALL GAME.
JUDGE HITS A LASER AND ON SIX
PITCHES OSUNA CLOSES IT OUT AND
A REALLY NICE WIN FOR THE
HOUSTON ASTROS.
DAVID: WELL PLAYED GAME.
TWO GREAT TEAMS BATTLING IT OUT.
GREAT JOB BY TANAKA KIND OF GOES
BY THE WAYSIDE.
ONLY TWO THREE-BALL COUNTS
TONIGHT
THE HOUSTON ASTROS FIND A WAY.
JON: YANKEES LED IT 3-1 AND
ASTR BACK, WIN IT@■ 4-3.
COMI■■■■
"SPORTSCENTER."
FOR DAVID ROSS, I'M JON SCIAMBI.
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VISIT NCICAP.ORG.]
GATORADE ZERO.
ALL THE ELECTROLYTES.
ZERO SUGAR.
♪♪
♪♪■■■■■R■R■■■?■■■
GET MORE OUT OF ZERO.
Staying at Hampton
for a work trip.
Oh no.
Your new boss
seems cool,
but she might not
be sweatpants cool.
Not quite ready
to face the day?
That's why we're here
with free hot breakfast.
Bompton.com for
our Price Match Guarantee.
Hampton by Hilton.
(PAUL)
How do we tell people they get
the best of both worlds
with Sprint?
Bompton.com for
our Price Match Guarantee.
(SASSBOT)
How about we get two-sport
legend, Bo Jackson...
(BO)
Sup?
Just tell peoplet aeed me
great network AND
a great price with Sprint.
(SASSBOT)
Yes! You can get an Unlimited
plan and a super cool all newu.
On an LTE advanced newtork
that's up to 2X faster than
before.
(EVELYN)
Bo does...know.
(VO)
Switch and get an
Unlimited plan with the
new Galaxy S10e lease included
for just $35 per month.
No trade-in required.
For people with hearing loss,
visit Sprintrelay.com
Incomparable design
makes it beautiful.
State of the art technology
makes it brilliant.
The visionary Lexus NX.
Lease the 2019 NX 300 for
$359 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
They didn't think they'd get
this far.
Or meet them,
or him.
■1
Or realise just how fun a road
trip could be
They discovered a new
favourite food,
a new favourite view.
And made some new favourite
memories.
...and Travel Like a Champion.
car hire on Expedia...ççç■■
Expedia
ANNOUNCER: THE BRAND NEW ESPN
APP.
NOW WITH ESPN+.
GET MORE ESPN AND DOWNLOAD NOW.
[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
ESPN, INC.]
ANNOUNCER: THIS IS
"SPORTSCENTER" AT NIGHT." ósZUB.
THE YANKEES LOOKING FOR THE
WORLD RECORD.
THE ROAD TO RESPECTABIL
TWO PLAYERS IN■ EPIC ■■z■z■z■n
UPON ARRIVAL, HE DID SOMETHING
THAT SHOCKED.
PLAT THE PODIUM.
THE COLLEGE BASKE■
CHAMPIONSHIP IS CROWNED.
>> BRYCEERSEY.
-- HARPER JERSEY.
>> HE LIKES THE DISCO INFERNO.
KENNY: WELCOME, EVERYONE, FOR
THIS EXTENDED PLAY VERSION OF
ESPN.
YOU DON'T DON'T WANT TO WATCH
THE VIRGINIA-TEXAS TECH GAME.
ZUBIN: WE'RE WATCHING THE GAME.
ABOUT EIGHT FEET AWAY ON A
MONITOR.
LET'S RUN THROUGH THE BEST OF
BASEBALL ON THIS MONDAY NIGHT.■
KE THE DIAMOND THEY
CALLX@■HIS.BLAKE SNEL■■ AND THE
THE WHITE SOX HERE.
NOW ABRY YOU.  CORNERS.
FIRST OUT OF THE INNING.
CASTILLO.
CAN'T CATCH UP TO THAT.
TWO OUTS.
THEY GOT HIM.
SIX INNINGS.
ONE EARNED RUN.
STRUCK OUT 11 AND THE RACE
IT BY A■ COUNT OF 5-1.
ZUBIN: BOTTOM LINE, THEY HAVE
PLAYED LESS THAN■ú 6% OF THEIR
GAMES.
NOBODY NEEDED AN OFFENSIVE
N THAN THEM■)■SOMEHOW BAEZ GETS
THAT AND IT DROPS.
5-0.
I DON'T KNOW W WOULD
SWING AT SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
MANAGES TO MAKE CONTACT.
A LITTLE SHRUG AFTERWARDS.
10-0 OVER THE PIRATES.
KENNY: ORIOLES-ATHLETICS.
KHRIS DAVIS.
ALBERTO.
FANCY PLAY.
WORKED A DOUBLE.
ENDORSED BY FRED MCGRIFF.
LAYING OUT.
MAKING THE TURN.
THEY GET THE OUT.
SHOWS HIS APPRECIATION.
ORIOLES GET OUT OF THE INNING.
A LOT OF D IN THIS GAME.
FIRES TO FIRST.
WATCH AG
TOP PLAY NOMINEES■■■■■E HERE.
ORIOLES ROB THE ATHLETICS YET
AGAIN.
SEVENTH INNING.
CHAPMAN TO THE PLATE.
PUTS THAT TO THIRD.
ANOTHER ONE.
HE DID AGAIN.
■ THE PLAY. ST■
WAITING FOR A SCORE IN THIS
THING.
ANYBODY.
12-4 I'M TOLD.■BIN: BRYCE HARPE
ILLIES, AND THE NATS.
THIS TIME THE REACTION A LITTLE
DIFFERENT.
YOU'LL GET 18 OR 19B■F THESE AR
YEAR.
VELASQUEZ CAME ON IN  LEAF.
BRYCE HARPER.
THEY ARE PLAYING HIM $330 ■/ú=■.
HE HAS SOME SKILLS.
NICE RELAY TO FINISH IT OFF.
HIS SECOND ASSIST OF THE SEASON.
NOTABLE BECAUSE HE HAD JUST ONE
ALL OF LAST YEAR.
FOR THAT MONEY YOU BETTER BE
ABLE TO DO A LITTLE BIT OF
EVERYTHING.
THE PHILLIES HAVEP POP.
THIS IS HERRERA.
2-4.
OME RUN.
KNOCKS HOME TWO.
HARPER HAS PLAYED WELL.
HERRERA HAS BEEN GREAT.
NOBODY HAS BEEN BETTER ON THE
THAN RHYS HOSKINS. ■■■■■@ SANC.
LIMITED HIS MOBILITY ON THE UND
THIRD STRAIGHT GAME WITH A HOME
RUN.
TIED FOR■=■y     THE SECí
STREAK IN HIS VERY YOUNG CAREER.
3-1 PITCH.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE HIS FOURTH
MULTIHOME RUN GAME OF HIS YOUNG
CAREER.
MUCH LIKE HERRERA.
2-4 WITH TWO HOME RUNS.
IN THE NINTH.
THE NATS TRY TO MOUNT A
COMEBACK.
DOZIER.
A LITTLE CLOSER.
4-2.
LET'S MAKE IT 4-3.■&88■■■]■■■■■■
TRUTH BE TOLD, THE NATS ARE NOT
TOO WORRIED■ ABOUT BRY■
MORE WORRI THEIR
BULLPEN.
MORE ON THAT IN A SECOND.
RUNNERS ON THIRD.
SUZUKI TO RIGHT.
HARPER BARELY HAS TO MOVE AND
THE PHILLIES WIN■
ON THE SEASON.
HOSKINS IS UP TO FIVE HOME RUNS.
TIED FOR THIRD MOST BY A
PHILLIES PLAYER IN THE TEAM'S
FIRST 10 GAMES IN THE EXPANSION
ERA.
REMEMBER, THE PHILLIES JUST
PLAYED NINE.
7-2 SO FAR.
THE ONLY PLAYERS TO HAVE MORE IN
PHILLIES HISTORY, THE GREATEST
PLAYER IN FRANCHISE HISTORY.
MIKE SCHMIDT AND THE GREAT CHASE
UTLEY.
TO THE NFL AND A GUY THAT IS
WELL KNOWN FOR NOT JUST ASKING
PEOPLE TO RELAX AND ELONGATE IT
AND TEST IT, AARON RODGERS
SEEMED A LITTLE BIT TESTY.
HE FIRED BACK MONDAY AND IT WAS
NOT RELAXED IN ANY FORM OR
FACTION.
>> IT IS NOT A MYSTERY.
THIS WAS A SMEAR ATTACK BY YOU
KNOW, A WRITER LOOKING TO
ADVANCE HIS CAREER, TALKING WITH
MOSTLY IRRELEVANT BITTER PLAYER■
WHO ALL HAVE AN AGENDA, WHETHER
THEY ARE ADVANCING THEIR OWN
CAREERS OR JUST TRYING TO STIR
OLD STUFF UP.
PART OF THE ARTICLE SEEMS TO■8■s
WANT TO SAY THE PACKERS AREX
WORRIED ABOUT ME AS THE LEADER
OF THE FOOTBALL TEAM MOVING
FORWARD.
IF THEY DID THAT, WHY WOULD THEY
RENETRACT LAST YEAR.
TWO,ALLY DISLIKED MIKE
THAT MUCH, WHY WOULD I RESIGNRp
WHAT WE DO AROUND HERE, IT IS
GOING TO BE ME AND MIKE MY
ENTIRE CAREER.
SO IF I REALLY DISLIKED HIM THAT
MUCH, DO YOU THINK I WOULD
RESIGN?
IS THE MONEY THAT IMPORTANT TO
ME?
I LOVE MIKE MCCARTHY.
MIKE HAS BEEN A HUGE PART OF MY
SUCCESS AND MY CAREER AND I'VE
HAD SOME AMAZING MOMENTS ON AND
OFF THE FIELD WITH MIKE.
ZUBIN: THAT'S PRETTY DARN
STRONG.
BECAUSE OF THAT KNEE INJURY THAT
COMPROMISE HIM HE HAS THE LOWEST
COMPLETION PERCENTAGE WHEN UNDER
DURESS.■@
KENNY: STICK WITH THE LOCAL
BASEBALL TEAM.
CLOSEST ONE TO GREEN BAY.
BREWERS-ANGELS.
CHRISTIAN YELICH.
HE IS A GOOD PLAYER.
IS IT GOING DROP?
YEAH, IT JUST DID.
IF WE DON'T SHOW BASERUNNING
ENOUGH OR SOMEBODY STEALING
HOME, CHECK OUT YELICH.
YELICH BEAT ■l■■ldz EASILY.[>SI
STEAL.
NO SCORE.
HOW ABOUT MAD BUM ON THE HILL.
MANNY MACHADO.
THE NEW PADRE.
HE COMPELLED THEM TO DO THAT.
SHOPPER AT THIRD.
GETS THE OUT.
BIG STARS DOING THINGS SO FAR.
NO STHIS OFAR.
'LL SEE IF IT PICKS UP FOR ONE
MAY GO PARTICULAR.
THE WORST SLUMP IN MAJOR LEAGUE
HISTORY.
KHRIS DAVIS HAS COMPANY, THOUGH.
IT HAPPENS TO BE NEARBY.
TIGER BACK AT■■@ AUGUSTA.
ALREADY MAKING A BIG MOVE.
WHAT'S THAT?
THE STAND CHANGE HE MADE THAT
COULD PUT HIM IN CONTENTION BY
SUNDAY.
"SPORTSCENTER" ROLLS ON.
■■ ■ ■ X
As a f advisor,nts
their minds in retirement.
You may have always
imagined your dream car
as something fast.
Then one day you decide
it just needs to be
safe enough to get her
to college and back.
Principal. We can help
you plan for that.
■■
I'm Paige, and well the little
thing that I like about the
Grilled Chicken Sandwich is
that it's perfect.
It's juicy and it just has
all the right combinations.
I think I could be considered
a Grilled Chicken Sandwich
influencer.
My name is Frank and the
little thing I like
about the Grilled Chicken
Sandwich is the first bite.■■
I love how juicy the chicken is
but there's also the tomatoes
and the lettuce and
it's incredible.
Make sure you get it
with waffle fries,
because that's my favorite.
KENNY: BACK WITH "SPER".
LET'S DO A FUTILITY.
DAVIS, HIS LAST HIT CAME LAST
BOTTOM OF OF TWO.
SINCE LAST SEPTEMBER.
GOT A BAT ON IT BUT■@■@■@■pHE O
PISCOTTY, 0 FOR HIS LAST 45.
NOW A CHANCE TO TRY SOME ROUGH
HISTORY.
JIMMY VELEZ.
LONGEST HISTORY AT 46.
THE HITLESS STREAK IS TIED WITH
THIS, OR IS IT?
NO.
THEY DROPPED THE BALL.
PROFAR GAV CHASE BUT IT DIDN'T
GO TO THE MITT.
NEW LIFE, BUT DAVIS IS GOING TO
TRY AGAIN.
HERE WE GO.
GOES THE OTHER WAY.
THEY HAD THE S
TIES THE VELEZ RECORD AT 46.
TRYING TO AVOID STEGGET■ RECORD
IN THE FIFTH INNING.
PUNCHES THAT THE OTHER WAY.
CATCH IS MADE AGAIN BY
GROSSMANN.
0-47.
A NEW MAJOR LEAGUE RECORD FOR
HITLESS MISS.
A LOT OF ZEROS IS WHAT WE'RE
GETTING HERE.
DAVIS 0-47 IN THE SEVENTH
INNING.
TRYING TO BREAK THINGS■@a@a@
BARNES AND NOBLE DOESN'T LET YOU
STAND AND DO NOTHING THAT LONG.
0-48.
ANOTHER SHOT.
EIGHTH INNING.
GOT HIM 0-49.
IT IS A DIFFICULT AND LONG,
PAINFUL EXPERIENCE FOR CHRIS
DAVIS NOW.
10 TIMES THE BATTED BALL DOES
NOT LEAVE THE INFIELD.
TWO R.B.I.'S IN THIS ONE.
ONE ON A BASES-LOADED WALK.
ANOTHER BY FIELDER'S CHOICE.
IT IS A SAD STATE OF AFFAIRS
AROUND THE BALTIMORE-WASHINGTON,
D.C. BELT WAY.
WE'RE NOT TRYING TO PILE ON
HERE.
THAT'S FOR PEOPLE ON TWITTER.
LAYING OUT THE FACTS.
FIRSTLY ON THE SORROWFUL CHRIS
DAVIS STREAK.
SEPTEMBER OF LAST YEAR.
HERE IT IS.
GLOVE.G THAT THING OVER THE
7ELF A DOUBLE BUT HE
HASN'T HAD A HIT SINCE
SINC LAST HIT, 550 PLAYERS
HAVE■z RECORDED A HIT FOR900
TOTAL HITS.■■■
EVEN BRANDON WOODRUFF
PITCHER IS 3-3 SINCE THEN.
CHRISTIAN YELICH HAS 37 HITS
SINCE HIS LAST HIT.
>> THIS IS ALLTIAN
YELICH.
>> HOW CAN ANYBODY BE THISD?@R
>> HE ■00 AMAZI■■■■á0
>> M.V.P.!
M.V.P.!
>> CHRIS  DAVIS.
AT SOME POINT HE HAS TO DO
SOMETHING.
KENNY: CHRISTIAN YELICH.
■  FORESHADOWING OF WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO COVER.
SINCE THAT L a DAVIS,
37 HITS.
MOST OF ANYONE.
THIS GUY ON FIRE.
CALL THE FIRE DEPARTMENT.
HOW ABOUT THE PITCHERS?
PITCHERS WITH A .120 BATTING
AVERAGE.
THAT IS BETTER THAN ZERO.
LET'S FIND A BRIGHT SPOT IN ALL
OF THIS.
HITTING THE BANK IN GREAT
POSITION.
HE HAS MADE A COUPLE OF MILLION
AND THE O'S STILL OWE HIM $100
MILLION UNTIL THE YEAR 2037.
ZUBIN: DAVIS IS NOT BUMMED OUT
BY THOSE NUMBERS, THAT'S FOR
SURE.
WITH REGARD TO MAKING POSITIVE
PROGRESS, WHETHER IT IS POLITICS
OR DAVIS OR IN THIS
PITCHING.
JOHN■MOLT BECAME THE FIRST■■■■■
PATIEN E■■
COOPERSTOWN.
HE HAS GONE FIVE STRAIGHT
APPEARANCES WITHOUT RECORDING AN
OUT AND DUE TO THE PROCEDURE,
LAST RECORDED AN OUT IN AUGUST
OF 2017!
YESTERDAY HE WAS BERATED BY
>> TREVOR ROS MR.
INFINITY STILL HAS NOT -- A
BATTER THIS YEAR.
>> ANOTHER WILD PITCH.
>> THAT WAS HIS -- THAT'S NINE
BATTERS THIS YEAR BY ROSENTHAL.
STILL NONE RETIRED.
>> THIS IS JUST AWFUL.
ZUBIN: THAT IS GARY COHEN, THE
TV PLAY BY PLAY VOICE OF THE
METS.
ME A LONG TIME, HE KNOWS  THE
AWFUL.
FOUR PITCHERS HAVE RECORDED OUTS
IN ONE PITCH THIS SEASON AND  ß
BETTER.
15 OUTS ON THE MOUND SO FAR■■■■
MURPHY WITH SIX.
TRYING TO GET THESE GUYS OFF THE
MOUND.
KENNY: WE SELECTED THE KINDEST
PERSON WHO WORKS FOR ESPN TO BE
INVOLVED IN THIS CHRIS DAVIS
THING SO WE COULD HANDLE IT
HUMANELY.
I KNOW HE IS GETTING RIPPED ON
SOCIAL MEDIA.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
IS THERE A COMBINATION OF THINGS
THAT LED TO THIS HORRIBLE
STREAK?
TIM: YES, THE BIGGEST FACTOR IS
THIS IS THE HARDEST GAME IN
WORLD TO PLAY.
A LOT OF PLAYERS HAVE SIMILAR
STREAKS LIKE THIS.
THIS JUST CAN'T HAPPEN IN OTHER
SPORTS LIKE IT DOES IN BASEBALL.
THIS IS AN NBA JUMP SH
MISSING 20 IN A ROW.
IN BASEBALL, GIVEN THE DEGREE OF
DIFFICULTY, THIS CAN HAPPEN.
THEN IT GETS IN YOUR HEAD.
OH, MY GOD, I'M NEVER GOING TO
GET ANOTHER HIT.
IT DOESN'T WORK THAT WAY IN
BASKETBALL.
A GREAT SHOOTER MISSES 15 IN A
ROW.
HE CAN'T WAIT TO SHOOT 16
BECAUSE HE KNOWS THIS IS GOING
IN.
CHRIS DAVIS HAS NO IDEA WHAT IS
GOING ON NOW.
EACH AT-BAT, EACH TIME HE
DOESN'T GET A HIT MAKES IT
WORSE.
KENNY: ARE HIS TEAMMATES SAYING
A LOT TO HIM OR LITTLE TO HIM?
IF YOU KEEP TALKING, IT MAKES
THE PROBLEM WORSE MAYBE BUT IF
YOU DON'T GIVE HIM ADVICE, HE IS
ON HIS OWN.
TIM: ALL OF THIS INFORMATION THE
HITTERS HAVE, IT IS NOT HELPING.
IF YOU HEAR TOO MUCH INFORMATION
IT PARALYZES YOU.
IF SOMEBODY SPEAKS TO YOU
BECAUSE YOU HAVEN'T GOT AN HIT
SINCE SEPTEMBER 14, THAT IS NOT
EASY EITHER.
DEALING WITH A TEAMMATE GOING
THROUGH THIS IS VERY, VERY HARD
ALSO.
KENNY: IF HE GETS A FEW HITS HE
WILL BE LIKE ALL RIGHT.
I'M BATTING .073.
TREVOR ROSENTHAL OF THE NATS HAS
NOT RECORDED AN OUT.
TIM: HE IS THE FIRST PLAYER
SINCE EARNED RUNS FOR MADE
OFFICIAL OVER 100 YEARS TO GO TO
MAKE FOUR APPEARANCES, HIS FIRST
FOUR APPEARANCES OF THE SEASON
AND NOT GET ANYBODY OUT.
HEy@ HAS9■■x AN INFINITY E.R.A.
AFTER FOUR APPEARANCES.
HE HAS FACED NINE BATTERS AND
RETIRED NONE OF THEM.
THAT HAS NOT HAPPENED IN OVER
100 YEARS.
TO HAVE STREAKS LIKE THESE
GOING, IF THESE TWO EVER FACED
EACH OTHER, IT WOULD BE LIKE THE
GREATEST THING I HAD EVER SEEN.
I WOULD HAVE TO RETIRE AFTER IT
BECAUSE IT COULDN'T GET ANY
BETTER THAN THIS.
KENNY: WHO IS GOING TO WIN THIS
RACE, A RIT FIRST OR AN OUT
FIRST IF YOU HAD TO PUT MONEY ON
IT?
OURIS■■■■■■■ DAVIS IS■2L2 GOING
A HIT SOON.
CHRIS  DAV■Q■■&■■E■= ON. ■ESE G.
SPEAKING AGAIN TO HOW DIFFICULT
THIS GAME CAN BE.
KENNY: TIM KURKJIAN, ENJOY THE
GAME.
I'M WISHING FOR SUCCESS FOR BOTH
OF THESE GUYS.
IT HAS GONE ON LONG ENOUGH.
TIM: ME TOO.
IT IS SAD.
IT REALLY IS.
KENNY: WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN WERE
THEY TOIFIES EACH OTHER?
THESE TWO TEAMS MEET EACH OTHER
LATER IN THE SEASON WHICH COULD
MAKE FOR AN INTERESTING■■■■■■■ M
BALTIMORE IN JULY AND THE OTHER
IN D.C. IN AUGUST.
ZUBIN: PLAYING ABOUT AS WELL AS
HE CAN POSSIBLY PLAY NOW.
THAT IS GOING TO GET THROUGH.
DEE GORDON CAN'T COME UP WITH
IT.
GETTING MORE THAN HALFWAY.
TOP SIX.
ENCARNACION.
GONE.
M'S LEAD 5-4.
NOW IT IS STILL THE SAME INNING
ZUBIN: ENCARNACION DOES PLAY ON.
THAT IS■8 GONúúú■■S SECOND@ @ ■,
THEY BOTH COME IN THE FRAME.
IT IS ALL MICHIGAN'S ALL NIGHT
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE POWER
RANKINGS.
THE DODGERS AND THE M'S ARE TOP.
IT IS 12-4, DODGERS, CARDLE NAL.
SOME SAY THE MARINERS ARE THE
BEST TEAM INr■ycy■■■y6=■;0#■■■■
RYU.
OUT OF THERE.
THE EXITw=ñ■o■ VELOCITY HAS BEC
THING HERE IN THE LAST FEW
YEARS.
115.3.
SCORCHING OUT OF THE PARK OR OUT
OF THE YARD IN 3.3 SECONDS.
THAT EXIT VELOCITY, HARDEST HIT
OF ANY HOME RUN THIS SEASON.
THEN WE START TO SETTLE DOWN.
THEN A LEFT GROIN STRAIN.
THEN WE MISSED SOME TIME LAST
SEASON.
PETERSON IS AT THE PLATE.
HE HAD QUITE THE OPENING DAY AS
YOU MAY RECALL.
A COUPLE OF HOME RUNS ON OPENING
DAY.
BACK AND FORTH WITH THE LONG
BALL.
ONE OF THREE GUYS.
COREY SEAGER.
THE OTHER WAY.
WELCOME BACK.
ALL HEALTH
THE ARE UP 3-2.
SAME SCORE IN THE SIXTH.
JOE KELLEY.
ON THE MOUND FOR THE DODGERS.
OF COURSE ONE OF THEIR NEW
ADDITIONS.
JOSE MARTINEZ AT THE PLATE.
THIS WILL DROP.■8
THE RE BIRDS TIE IT AT 3-3.
TWO BATTERS LATER.
DEJONG IS AT THE PLATE.
WE HAVE A RUNNER ON THIRD.
THAT'S WILD.
GOLDSCHMIDT COMES IN TO SCORE.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, THAT WOULD
END UP BEING THE RUN TO WIN THE
GAME.
ST. LOUIS, FOUR, DODGERS FINALLY
FF AT THREE.
KENNY: ROCKIES TRAILING THE
BRAVES 7-3 IN THE FIFTH.
TWO ON, THREE OUT FOR TREVOR
STORY.
NOW A HOME RUN.
HIS FOURTH OF THE SEASON.
ROCKIES TRAIL THISNG
COUNT OF 7-6.
THEY GOT LOTS TO
THEY ARE IN THE SIXTH INNING.
TONIGHT, A BUNCH OF US STOOD
AROUND THE TV AND WATCHED THE
GUYS NOT GET A HIT.
45 YEARS AGO THE WHOLE NATION
WATCHING TVSEE HAMMERING
HANK SET THE NEW HOME RUN
RECORD.
WE'RE LOOKING BACK AT THAT AND
ALL HOMERS REAL SEASON.
TIGER MAKES A BIG CHANGE.
WHAT DID HE DO AT AUGUSTA THAT
MIGHT BE A GAME CHANGER ON THE
COURSE WHEN PLAY BEGINS.
>> TECH: At Safelite AutoGlass,
we really pride ourselves
on making it easy
to get your windshield fixed.>r
science papers.
>> TECH VO: This teacher always
puts her students first.
>> STUDENT: I did mine
on volcanoes.
>> TEACHER: You did?! Oh, I
can't wait to read it.
>> TECH VO: So when she had
auto glass damage...
she chose Safelite.
With Safelite, she could see
exactly when we'd be there.
>> TEACHER: You must be Pascal.
.
>> TECH VO: Saving her time...
[HONK, HONK]
>> KIDS: Bye!
>> TECH VO: ...so she can save
the science project.
>> KIDS: Whoa!
>> KIDS VO: ♪ Safelite repair,
Safelite replace ♪
♪
(VO)
I know what you're thinking.
Electric, it's not for you.
And, you're probably right.
Electric just doesn't
have enough range.
It will never
survive the winter.
Charging stations?
Good luck finding one of those.
So, maybe an electric car
isn't for you after all.
Or, is it?
♪
No one knows what the future
■■■■■
of transportation
will look like.
Robots!■
But no matter what,
Enterprise can help.
You can rent a car
for a road trip...
Look kure!■■
Cool.
You can rent a truck for a
move...
...You can buy a car...
...Commmute in a vanpool...
Or get picked up because your
car is in a pool.
My bad!
Count on Enterprise,
no matter where
transportation goes next.
Let's go!
I love the future.
(VO) How can Enterprise
pick you up today?
■
TIM■■Ñ■ How can Enterprise
pick you up today?
>MY LAWN.
IT'S BEEN WORN DOWN
Y THIN GRASS!
NOW THERE'S SCOTTS THICK'R LAWN,
WITH A SOIL IMPROVER
TO STRENGTHEN ROOTS!
THE REVOLUTIONARY 3-IN-1
SOOR WEA■Ñ2■2
SEED TO FILL IN GAPS!
■/  AND ñED!
UP TO
A 50% THICKE
AFTER JUST ONE APPLICATION.
♪ ♪ ♪
NOW YARD TIME IS OUR TIME.
THISç■TS YARD.
Can.
Can't.
♪ ♪
Can.
With just 1.7 Carbs and 62 Cals,
you CAN enjoy a Michelob a week.
>> I JUST LOVE PLAYING.
IT HAS A PLACE IN MY HEART.■>■>
I JUST MISS
COMPETING.c/■@■&■&E
>> TIGER WOODS IS NOW DRIVING.
>> MY WHOLE GOAL IS TO BEAT YOU.
KENNY: ONE TIME FOR ONE OF OUR
PRETEND GOLF STORIES I ASKED
TIGER WOODS IF HE WOULD GO ALONG
WITH A PRETEND STORY ABOUT HOW
MUCH HE LOVED IT WHEN PEOPLE
TOOK PICTURES AND CAMERAS MADE
SHUTTER NOISES IN HIS BACKSWING.
HE SAID NO.
HE PROBABLY STILL HATES SHUTTER
NOISE IN HIS BACKSWING BUT HE
WOULD ACCEPT IT IF HE HAD HIS
OLD SWING BACK.
HE IS NOT THE ONLY ONE PLAYING
IF THE MASTERS.
IT IS UP NOW TO OUR GOLF TEAM AT
AUGUSTA TO PAINT THE FULL
PI
>> GREETINGS FROM AUGUSTA
NATIONAL.
THIS FIRST DAY OF THE WEEK.
83RD MASTERS COMING THURSDAY.
SUN WAS OUT EARLY.
WARM DAY.
SOME THUNDERSTORMS CAME M■■■LTHA
EAIGER WOODS.
■8 YEARS REMOVED FROM HIS LAST
TRIUMPH HERE AND STUCK ON 14
MAJOR CHAMPIONSHIPS BUT THE
FOUR-TIME MASTERS CHAMPION
CAPTAIN VATES EVEN ON A MONDAY
AS HE ENJOYED A PRACTICE ROUND
WITH FRED COUPLES.
AND JUSTIN THOMAS.
EVEN THOUGH HE IS 14 YEARS
REMOVED FROM HIS LAST WIN HERE,
SO MUCH OF HOW WE VIEW THIS ZOR
PARTICULAR THROUGH THE LENS OF
TIGER WOODS, WHAT IS HE WORKING
ON?
>> WOODS IS AS MUCH A CREATURE
OF HABIT AS ANYONE ON TOUR.
ONE BREAK THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN,
OUT SHARP AT 8:00 A.M. OFF THE
10 TEE ON MONDAY BEFORE THE
HEAVIER WEATHER ROLLED IN
GSIDE JUSTIN THOMAS r/D FREDN?=M
WAY OVER TO THE PRACTICE AREA
AND PUT IN AN HOUR PLUS THERE AS
WELL.
ON SUNDAY LATE IN THE AFTERNOON
WOODS ARRIVED AND SPENT NEARLY
THREE HOURS ON THE COURSE WITH
ON■■■■ WEDGES ANDñ■ñ■ PUTTER.
HITTINGñ■ SHOTS ESSENTIALLYñ■ñ■
100 YARDS AND IN TRYING TO DIAL
HERE AND HAVING SUCCESS AT  NG
AUGUSTA NATIONAL.
WOODS DID MAKE A VISIT LAST WEEK
ON WEDNESDAY AND ACCORDING TO
THOSE WHO WERE PLAYING WITH HIM,
PLAYED WELL, CARDED A 65 Pñ■ñ■ñ■
MCNAMARA.ñ■
SOME PARTS OF THE PREPARATION
STICñ■■■■■
■■BIT DIFFERENT.
WITH THE WEATHER, WE'LL SEE HOW
THAT AFFECTS THE PREPARATION
GOING FORWARD.
>> THANK YOU.
ALONGSIDE MY FRIEND ANDY NORTH.
AS HE WAS TALKING ABOUT THE
WEDGES AND THE PUTTERS, YOU WERE
NODDING YOUR HEAD.
WHY?
>> IF YOU HAVE BEEN ON A BOAT IN
THE PACIFIC, YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND HOW POORLY TIGER'S
I THOUGHT INY HE■b■ñ■■■■>>■■■LE
E FACT THAT HE IS THROUGHOUT
DOING SOME THINGS THAT HELP YOU
WIN HERE, TO GET THE BALL UP AND
IN TO, MAKE THAT 8-FOOTER FROM
PAR, TO TWO-PUTT FROM 14, 15
FEET AWAY.
YOU CAN NEVER CAN PLAY THIS
COURSE TOO MUCH.
>> YOU CAN'T MASTER THIS
PARTICULAR GOLF COURSE EVEN AS
WELL AS YOU UNDERSTAND IT.
TOM ALLUDED TO THE WEATHER.
HE SAID IT WAS GREAT.
IT WAS FAST.
SINCE THEN, WE HAVE HAD A LOT OF
THIS.
WHERE DOES THAT LEIGH THINGS ON
MONDAY?
>> THE GOLF COURSE WAS SOFTER
THAN THEY PROBABLY WOULD HAVE
LIKED.
THEY ARE TALKING AN INCH OR TWO
OVER THE NEXT 24 HOURS.
IF THAT HAPPENS, THAT WILL BE A
PROBLEM.
WE HAVE THE SUBAIR SYSTEM HERE
TO SUCK THE MOISTURE OUT OF THE
GREENS BUT IT STILL IS NOT GOING
TO GET THE FIRMNESS THEY HAD A
COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO.
>> EXPERIENCE HERE IS SO
CRITICAL.
THOSE WHO KNOW IT WELL KNOW COME
THURSDAY MORNING NO MATTER WHAT
THEY HAVE SEEN IT IS GOING TO
LOOK DIFFERENT.
I'M HAPPY TO SEE TWENDS WEATHER
LOOKS FANTASTIC.
MY FAVORITE DAY OF THE WEEK
HERE.
PAR 3 CONTEST.
WE HAVE A PREVIEW SHOW HERE AS
WELL.
BETWEEN NOW AND THEN, A LOT OF
HARD WORK WILL GO IN AS FOLKS
TRY TO FIGURE OUT HOW THE SLIP
ON A GREEN JACKET.
JOHNSON IS NOW DOWN TO SECOND IN
THE WORLD GOLF RANKINGS.
HE WAS SURPLANTED AT THE TOP BY
THIS MAN, JUSTIN ROSE.
HE HASN'T BEEN FITTED WITH A
JACKET YET.
IT WOULD NOT SHOCK ANYONE IF
D.J. OR JUSTIN WERE TO BREAK
THROUGH THIS YEAR AT THE
MASTERS.
KENNY: WE USED TO PLAY IN
WASHINGTON WHERE WE WOULD THROW
AND PUTT.
JUST NEED A PUTTER.
NOT AS BIG A DEAL AS WEDNESDAY.
FAMILY ORIENTED TRADITION
STARTED IN 1960.
THE MASTERS PAR 3 CONTEST NOON
EASTERN.
YOU CAN JUST GO TO AUGUSTA.
>> WAITING.
INTO DEEP LEFT CENTER FIELD.
GOES BACK.
BANGS IT INSIDE.
WHAT A MARVELOUS MOMENT FOR
BASEBALL.
WHAT A MARVELOUS MOMENT FOR THE
COUNTRY AND THE WORLD.
AT 9:10 IN ATLANTA, GEORGIA.
HENRY AARON HAS ECLIPSED THE
MARK SET BY BABE RUTH.
KENNY: I'M OLD ENOUGH TO HAVE
SEEN THAT LIVE.
HENRY AARON.
HITS ANOTHER HOME RUN.
RONALD ACUNA JR. PUMPS THAT
THING THE OTHER WAY.
OVER SOME FENCING THAT HAD BEEN
ESTABLISHED BEFORE THE GAME.
29R HOMER.
HE IS JUST 7■■    BE GREAT
HANK AARON.
ZUBIN: HOW YOUNG HE IS.■(■=■■y■1
SCHWARBER.
CUBS UNLOADED TODAY ON THE
BUCCOS 10-0.
HE IS A MEASLY 680 TO TIE
HAMMERING HANK AS WE CELEBRATE
THAT ANNIVERSARY.
KENNY: THE A'S AND ORIOLES.
WE SAW SOME HITLESSNESS IN THIS
GAME.
WE ALSO SAW THIS.■ó■■oo■■s■■a+u
TRE MANCINI.
COUGHS THAT THE OTHER WAY.
66TH OF HIS CAREER.EE
BEHINDENRY AARON.
ZUBIN: THIS IS WHY BASEBALL IS
SO GREAT.
NOBODY HAD A BETTER WEEKEND THAN
DANIEL VOGELBACH.
HE WENT YARD A COUPLE OF TIMES.
YESTERDAY GOES DEEP HERE.
FOUR STRAIGHT GAMES WITH A HOME
RUN FOR DANIEL VOGELBACH.
746 BEHIND THE TRUE HOME RUN
CHAMPION.
KENNY: DODGERS AND CARDINALS.
CARDS DOWNJ 2-0.
MARCELL OZUNA QUICKLY OUT.
WE HAVE THE EXIT VELOCITY.
115.3.
HARDEST HIT HOME RUN THIS
SEASON.
121ST OF HIS CAREER.
WAY BACK.
UPDATE.
WE GOT SOME BREWERS AND THE
ANGELS.
WE WERE HYPING CHRISTIAN YELICH
EARLIER.
CHECK HIM OUT IN DEFENSE.
RACING FOR IT.
WAIT.
GET UP AND THROW.
UH-OH.
ALBERT PUJOLS, GET BACK.
DO NOT.
KIND OF AN AREA CALL THERE.
SEE IT AGAIN.
TAKE A LOOK ONE MORE TIME.
THERE IS THE CATCH.
■;h; SOLID.
ALBERT PUJOLS IS EXPECTING THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOINGROW AND GET HIM
OUT AT SECOND.
ISOLATION REEL.
GET BACK!
HERE IS THE THROW.
HE IS ON.
OUT AT SECOND.
WAY BACK!
LA STELLA IS OUT OF THE YARD.
CAME BACK IN.
BUT IT WAS GONE.
THAT IS A HOME RUN.
A TWO-RUN JOB.
WHAT HAVE WE GOT FOR A SCORE
HERE?
2-1, EARLY ACTION.
WE'LL UPDAVID DATE THIS AS OUR
FIVE-HOUR SHOW CONTINUES HERE
FROM BRISTOL, CONNECTICUT.S÷÷■[8
1BIN: NOT TO BE PICKY HERE.
ALBERT PUJOLS COULD HAVE SLIP
THERE HAD.
COMING UP, HARDEN, INSIDE THE
♪ ♪
Plants capture CO2.
What if other kind■ed it too?■■
If these industrial plants had
tech■=■=Ñ;■;ç;ç;ç;ñ;x
that captured carbon like trees
we could help lower emissions.
Carbon Capture is important
technology -
and experts agree.
That's why we're working on ways
to improve it.
So plants...
can be a little more...
d>d>■>
♪ ♪
like plants.
Bonvoy.
[M
[Music]
Bonvoy.
BONVOY.
[Music]
Bonvoy.
Discover the new
language of travel.
Bonvoy.
Marriott Bonvoy.
30 hotel brands.
Endless experiences.
Rewards reimagined.
[Music]
GATORADE ZERO.
ALL THE ELECTROLYTES.
Rewards reimagined.
ZERO SUGAR.
♪♪
GET MORE OUT OF ZERO.■■Ñ■■:
Let's see, ALEVE is
proven better on pain
than Tylenol Extra Strength.
And last longer
with fewer pills.
So why am I still
thinking about this?
I'll take Aleve.
ALEVE.
Proven better on pain.
■/■7
Boom! Another alert from Capital
One's lil' robot banker, ENO!
C'mon man!
What're you doin'??
Man, I love alerts.
Alert! End of half!
Alert! Jalapeño poppers!
Alert! I just made two identical
purchases at AIR-HORNZ.com?
Alert! It's true,
because I love to....
You have got to stop!
ALERT! No, I don't! ALERT!
KENNY: LET'S GET BACK TO THAT
BREWERS-ANGELS THING.
INTERESTING DEVELOPMENT HERE.
CHRISTIAN YELICH.
JUST SAW HIM CLOSE OUT ALBERT
PUJOLS.
YELICH AT THE PLATE.
LAUNCHES THAT.
OF55555■■■■■■/■/■á■á■á■á■á■á■á■
YEçá■■■vv THE D AND TROUT
RIGHT BACK TO HIM.
L.A. UP 2-1 ON MILWAUKEE.
IT IS EARLY ON.
WE'LL FOLLOW THIS THING AS
EVENTS DICTATE.
2-1 I SAID.
THAT IS YOUR SCORE.
THAT'S MIKE TROUT.■#ó
>> ♪ HOW ABOUT THAT ■d
HOW ABOUT THAT ♪♪
ZUBIN: THERE IS A NOTION IN THE
NBA THE LEAGUE LOVES TO AWARD
THE SHINY NEW ENTITY WITH THE
M.V.P. AWARD.
AFTER ALL EVEN THOUGH MICHAEL
JORDAN WON AN M.V.P. FIVE TIMES
HE ONLY WITH WON IT BACK-TO-BACK
ONCE.
JAMES HARDEN MIGHT DESERVE IT
AGAIN BUT GIANNIS MIGHT GET IT
AGAIN.
>> HARDEN!
>> JAMES HARDEN!
>> I DON'T THINK THERE IS ONE
GUY THAT CAN STOP HIM.
>>
ZUBIN: --
>> HARDEN OR GIANNIS.
WHO TAKES HOME THE HARDWARE?
I AM GOING TO MAKE THE KICE WHY
IT SHOULD BE ANTETOKOUNMPO.
>> THE HARDEN SHOW.
>> HARDEN■O 36 A GAME WITH A 30
EFFICIENCY RATING.
THAT'S WHAT HE IS DOING NOW
YOU KNOW WHO NEVER DID THAT?
SHAQ.
TIMMY NEVER DID IT EITHER.
NOT EVEN MICHAEL JORDAN.
WILT CHAMBERLAIN THE■■■■■■■■■■■
LEVEL.
FROM 1961-1964.
>> HE HAD A PERFECT -- SINCE
YOU'RE REALLY GR ON HISTORY,
YOU'LL PROBABLY REMEMBER WHEN
WILT WAS DOING ALL OF THAT.
HOW MANY M.V.P. AWARDS DID HE
GET?
NONE.
OBVIOUSLY THOSE NUMBERS DON'T
MEAN ANYTHING.
>> SHOWTIME.
ANTETOKOUNMPO WITH THE HAMMER.
>> HERE IS THE REASON AMONG THEN
MANY I THINK GIANNIS IS GOING TO
WIN.
FOR THE THIRD STRAIGHT SEASON HE
IS LEADING THE BUCKS IN POINTS,v
ASSISTS AND REBOUNDS.@v
ON TOP OF THAT, WHEN THE M.V.P.
RACE HAS COME BACK, THE BEST
PLAYER ON THE BEST TEAM AND THE
LEAGUE'S LEADING■,■,■,■,■, SCOR
BEST PLAYER ON THE BEST TEAM HAS
WON THE M.V.P. EIGHT TO HAVE
LAST 10 TIMES UNDER THAT
PARTICULAR CIRCUMSTANCE.
THE TRUTH IS THAT GIANNIS IS WAY
MORE VALUABLE THAN JAMES HARDEN.
>> GIANNIS ON THE BREAK.
HE IS UNSTOPPABLE!
KENNY: A WELL EXECUTED FUN
DEBATE.
THESE ARE INDISPUTABLY THE "TOP
PLAYS."
NUMBER 10.
BA THROWS.
THELE ON TH■8ú
WE NEED TO SEE THAT AGAIN.
SURE.
CUBS WIN IT 10-0.
ZUBIN: MAYBE THAT IS THE CHRIS
DAVIS SOLUTION.
BOTTOM FIVE.
PISCOTTY IS GOING THE MAKE A
NICE LONG RUN.
SLIDES IN TO MAKE THE GRAB.
WE WILL SEE THE A'S AND O'S
LATER HERE ON "TOP PLAYS."
KENNY: WHAT I LIKE TO CALL ASIAN
FOOTBALL CONFEDERATION SOCCER.
DEL MAKES THE PASS.
BANGS IT ON IN.
SADLY HIS TEAM LOST 4-1.
THAT IS A PRETTY GOOD GOAL.
ZUBIN: BASEBALL TO ASIAN
FOOTBALL TO SOFTBALL.
LITERA■ÑG EVERY
SPORTING EVENT ON PLANET EARTH
ON "SPORTSCENTER."
THE■= DIVING GRAB.9
PROBABLY A LITTLE BETTER THAN
PISCOTTY'S.
10-9.
KENNY: CH RINCH S -- CHRIS
DAVIS.
ROBERTO, THE FANCY DOUBLE PLAY.
A LOT OF GOOD DEFENSE IN THAT
GAME.
ORIOLES WIN IT EASILY 12-4.
ZUBIN: CONNECTICUT HIGH SCHOOL
BASEBALL.
I'M TELLING YOU WE'RE DIGGING
DEEP.
DANIEL.
THIS IS -- ACROSS THE DIAMOND.
THREE GREAT "WEB GEM"S SO FAR.
KENNY: BACK TO THE PHILLIES AND
NATIONALS.
SUZUKI PUTS THE BAT ON IT.
BARE HAND.
ZING IT ACROSS.
JUST IN TIME.
THAT IS A BIG PLAY.
THAT IS A MAJOR LEAGUE PLAY.
PHILLIES WIN IT.
THEY ARE IN THE MAJOR LEAGUE.
ZUBIN: I'M GOING TO TOP THE
ASIAN CONFEDERATION.
TURKISH SUPER LEAGUE.
UPPER 90'S.
NINE TALLEYS IN ALL IN THIS
GAME.
KENNY: ASTROS AND YANKS.
URSHELA.
BREGMAN.
DID A COUPLE OF THINGS.
GOT THE WINNING RUN IN FACT.
ASTROS WIN 4-1.
ZUBIN: NUMBER ONE.
SOCCER.
A SPORT WE HAVE HEARD OF.
CHELSEA AND UNITED.
TERRIFIC.
CHELSEA 2-0 WIN.
MORE "SPORTSCENTER" RIGHT NOW.