BOMANI: ON A STRING.
PABLO: THE CONDUCTOR IS LIKE
NO, YOU CANNOT OPERATION DUMBO
DROP INTO MY TRAIN.
NO, YOU CANNOT DO THAT.
BO, YOU ARE A SUBWAY RIDER WITH
MORE DILIGENCE THAN ME.
DO YOU HAVE SYMPATHY FOR ANY OF
THE CHARACTERS INVOLVED IN THIS
SCENE?
BOMANI: I DON'T JUST HAVE
SYMPATHY FOR THE CONDUCTOR.
I WANT THAT GUY TO GET
PAPI: I LIKE CHEESE.
DAN: WELCOME TO A SMOOTH AND
SILKY "HIGHLY QUESTIONABLE."
LOOK AT HIM.
SO VERY SOUTH BEACH.
CHRIS BOSH, WHAT DO YOU LIKE ON
THE SHOW TODAY?
CHRIS: I LIKE THAT I'M HERE.
DAN: OKAY.
NARCISSISM AT ITS FINEST.
PAPI?
PAPI: CHRIS BOSH, WHO WAS A
BETTER PLAYER, PAUL PIERCE OR
DUANE WADE?
DAN: PAUL PIERCE IS A HALL OF
FAME PLAYER, BUT DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE IT.
LISTEN TO THIS.
>> WHO'S THE BETTER NBA PLAYER?
>> THAT'S EASY.
I CAN SAY THAT OFTEN THE BAT,
THAT'S ME.
IF YOU GIVE ME SHAQ, IF YOU GIVE
ME LEBRON --
>> WHAT ABOUT THREES?
>> WE GOT THAT LATE.
I'M TALKING ABOUT EARLY IN MY
CAREER.
>> WHAT WOULD HAVE BEEN A
PERFECT TIME FOR YOU, PAUL?
>> WHEN I WAS 24 YEARS OLD, GIVE
ME SHAQ.
I'M 25, GIVE ME LEBRON OR BOSH,
I'M SITTING ON FOUR OR FIVE
CHAMPIONSHIPS EASILY.
>> WITH WHO?
>> ANTOINE WALKER.
>> COME ON, MAN.
DAN: OH, HE WASN'T DONE, THOUGH.
JALEN ROSE LET HIM HAVE IT.
LISTEN THAT.
>> SINCE DWYANE WADE ISN'T HERE
TO 2010 HIS HONOR, IT'S MY TURN.
NO BACKTRACK.
HE'S BEEN AN ALL NBA FIRST TEAM
TWICE.
PAUL HASN'T DONE IT.
HE MADE ALL NBA EIGHT TIMES TO
YOUR FOUR.
HE MADE ALL DEFENSIVE TEAM THREE
TIMES TO YOUR ZERO.
HE'S WON SCORING TITLE.
YOU WEREN'T ABLE TO WIN THE
SCORING TITLE.
HE HAS THREE RINGS.
YOU HAVE ONE RING.
>> OOH, THREE IS BETTER THAN
ONE.
DAN: YOU DON'T WANT MY OPINION
ON THIS, HIS OPINION ON THIS.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
CHRIS BOSH, WHAT WAS YOUR
REACTION WHEN YOU HEARD PAUL
PIERCE SAY HE WAS BETTER THAN
DWYANE WADE?
CHRIS: WE GOT TO STOP COMPARING
GUYS.
THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
WE SHOULDN'T BE HAVING THESE
CONVERSATIONS.
HE WALK INTO THAT.
THEY KNEW WHAT THEY WERE DOING.
PAUL PIERCE IS A COMPETITIVE
GUY.
HE'S WON CHAMPIONSHIPS, GOING TO
THE HALL OF FAME.
IF YOU ASK HIM WHO'S BETTER,
HE'S GOING TO SAY HIMSELF.
100%■■■■■RY TIME.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT'S --
DAN: BUTWRONG.
EY, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
AY DWYANEADE IS TOUGH
TO BEAT.
DAN: THAT'S L
WE'LL# HEAT UP HIS OPINIONS
AROUND HERE.
DWYANE WADE IS TOUGH TO BEAT.
PAPI: DO YOU KNOW WHO THESE TWO
GUYS ARE BETTER THAN?
DAN: WHO'S THAT?
PAPI: LEBRON.
I TELL YOU ONE THING, HE GOT
MORE LOSSES IN THE FINALS, AND
LEBRON GOT ALL THE LOSSES IN THE
FINALS.
THESE TWO GUYS DON'T GOT THAT
MANY LOSSES IN THE FINALS, YOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
HE'S WERE THE.
LEBRON IS THE WORST OF THE
THREE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
DAN: IT'S THE ONLY THING YOU CAN
DO.
THAT'S THE PROPER RESPONSE TO
THAT.
THAT HURT HIS STOMACH.
[LAUGHTER]
PAPI: YOU GO AHEAD, COUNT THE
LOSSES.
DAN: I MEAN, THERE ARE MORE
HE'S RIGHT.
HE'S RIGHT ABOUT THE NUMBER OF
LOSSES THIS THE FINALS.
PAPI: WHAT'S THE POINT ABOUT
GETTING TO THE FINALS?
STAY HOME.
DAN: ALL RIGHT, STAY HOME.
PAPI: HE'S STAYING HOME THIS
YEAR.
DAN: HE'S NOT GOING TO LOSE IN
THE FINALS THIS YEAR.
PAPI: DOES KEVIN DURANT DESERVE>
HEAT FOR JOINING THE WARRIORS?
LISTEN.
DAN: LISTEN TO THIS.
>> RUN IT BACK, SAME TEAM.
RIGHT?
RUN IT BACK.
DON'T CHANGE TEAMS.
THAT'S HOW WE GREW UP, RIGHT?
RUN IT BACK, SAME TEAM.
YOU DON'T WANT TO CHANGE
ANYTHING.
WE FEEL WE'RE THE BETTER TEAM.
WE JUST DIDN'T PLAY WELL ENOUGH,
SO LET'S RUN IT BACK.
THEY DIDN'T DO THAT.
THEY WERE, LIKE, WE NEED TO
RELOAD, GET OUR BIG BROTHER.
OH, THANKS, GUYS.
THAT'S FUN.
DAN: SO OF COURSE KEVIN DURANT
CAN'T LET THIS STAN, CHRIS BOSH,
BECAUSE HE'S ALWAYS LURKING
AROUND INSTAGRAM ACCOUNTS.
EVERYBODY FROM THE STREETS NOW.
YOU GOT RICHARD JEFFERSON.
READ THAT FOR YOURSELF.
CHRIS, WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS
HERE?
WHY IS KEVIN DURANT FIGHTING
WITH EVERYBODY ON TWITTER?
CHRIS: K.D., LEAVE IT ALONE, MY
BROTHER.
I DON'T KNOW.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS GOING
TO HAVE SOMETHING TO SAY.
IF YOU'RE A FREE AGENT, YOU CAN
GO WHERE YOU WANT TO GO.
SO IF YOU WANT TO GO TO THE
WARRIORS, GO TO THE WARRIORS.
ONLY PROBLEM IS TAKING THE
CRITICISM.
SO FOR HIM IT'S JUST COME
ABSURDLY INSANELY HIGH.
DAN: THINGS DON'T ALWAYS GO THE
WAY YOU EXPECT THEM TO.
WHEN H HERE, HE THOUGHT
HE'D BE THE LEADING SCORER ON
MIAMI HEAT.
THAT'S A THING HE THOUGHT.
DIDN'T TAKE HIM LONG TO FIGURE
OUT, WAIT A MINUTE, THESE GUYS
HOLD ON TO THE BALL.
PAPI: YOU KNOW WHAT I WOULD DO
IF I WERE DURANT?
DAN: WHAT'S THAT, PAPI?
PAPI: I'M GOING TO STA■÷■÷■÷■÷ ÷
WARRIORS.
CR■÷■÷■÷,÷FTER THAT I'LL÷■÷■÷■÷÷
SHOW YOU THE FINGER WITH THE
RING ON.
ONE RING ON EACH THAN FINGER.
SCREW UP, ALL RIGHT?
THAT'S WHAT I WOULD DO RIGHT
NOW.
I TELL YOU WHAT, WHEN YOU WIN
MORE CHAMPIONSHIPS AND YOU GET
MORE RINGS, YOU CAN JAM THEM
INTO THOSE FINGERS THAT YOU
HAVE, YOU KNOW, KEEP JAMMING
THEM IN THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
KEEP JAPPING THEM, THAT'S RIGHT,
THAT'S RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
DAN: I MEAN, YOU CAN DO THAT.
PAPI: ARE YOU EXCITED TO WATCH
GREAT DEFENSE TONIGHT?
DAN: OH, GOD, NO.
THIS IS THE WORST THANK YOU THAT
I CAN HAVE IMAGINED HERE,
BECAUSE I CAN'T TELL THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN BAD
BASKETBALL AND GOOD DEFENSE.
I KNOW THESE TWO TEAMS
STATISTICALLY ARE VERY GOOD AT
DEFENSE.
I ALSO KNOW THEY SLOWED DOWN THE
PACE INTO THE MUCK.
I'M NOT HERE TO WATCH 22-
BASKETBALL AT THE HALF.
CHRIS BOSH, DO YOU APPRECIATE
THE DEFENSIVE EFFORT?
IT WAS AN UNDERRATED PARENT OF
YOUR CHAMPIONSHIP TEAMS?
YOU GUYS WERE GREAT AT DEFENSE.
CHRIS: WELL, DEFENSE DOES WIN
CHAMPIONSHIPS.
IN TODAY'S GAME, I THINK IT'S
INTERESTING TWO DEFENSIVE TEAMS
ARE PLAYING IN THE CHAMPIONSHIP
FOR THE NCAA.
AS FAST AS THE GAME IS, AS MANY
THREES AS WE'RE SHOOTING NOW,
IT'S BECOME A■■■■■■■■UT SES■■
WE'RE GOING TO DO THAT FOR THE
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP.
DAN: I KNOW, AND I DON'T WANT TO
WATCH IUSE IT LOOKS LIKE
PEACH BASKET BASKETBALL.
I LIKE ROCKET LAUNCHERS FROM
HALF COURT.
I'M NOT INTERESTED INASMUCH AS
TWO ANONYMOUS TEAMS, TWO COME
FROM NOWHERE TEAMS THAT PLAY A
STYLE OF BASKETBALL THAT'S NOT
APPETIZING.
PAPI SOMETIMES■■NSE
BEATS GOOD DEFENSE.
DAN: OH, NO.
WHAT'S HE GOING TO SHOW US HERE?
OH, COME ON!
COME ON!
I TAUGHT WE WEREN'T DOING THIS
ANYMORE TO HIM.
I THOUGHT WE AGREED IN THE
PRESHOW MEETING TODAY WE WERE
GOING TO MAKE FUN OF ME, NOT
HIM!
PAPI: IS TRICKY NICKY ACTUALLY
LOOKING OUT FOR THE BEST
INTERESTS OF HIS PLAYERS WHEN HE
TELLS THEM TO RETURN TO SCHOOL?
DAN: HE MAKES A LOT GOOD POINTS
HERE.
IT COULD BE SELF-INTERESTED
POINTS NONETHELESS THE TRUE.
LISTEN TO THIS.
>> WE HAVE FIFTH-ROUND GRADES,
FREE AGENT GRADES, GOING OUT FOR
THE DRAFT.
YOU KNOW, THE PERSON THAT LOSES
IN THAT IS THE PLAYER.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE A THIRD-ROUND
DRAFT PICK, AND WE HAD ONE HERE
LAST YEAR, I'M NOT MENTIONING
NAMES, GOES AND STARTS FOR HIS
TEAM, SO HE'S MAKING THIRD ROUND
MONEY WHICH IS NOT THAT GREAT.
BE THE FIRST GUY TAKEN AT HIS
POSITION THIS YEAR PROBABLY AND
MAKE $15 MILLION, $18 MILLION
MORE.
THE AGENT AND CLUB MAKE OUT.
NOW YOU'VE GOT A GUY TO PLAY FOR
THAT KIND OF MONEY FOR THREE
YEARS.
AWRIGHT?
GET TO THE NEXT CONTRACT, 50% OF
THESE GUYS ARE NEVER GETTING TO
A NEXT CONTRACT.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN ALL OF US GOT
TO ONE EITHER.
DAN: IT DOESN'T MEAN THEY WON'T
GET HURT, WON'T GET MONEY, AND
PLAYED ANOTHER YEAR FOR■ FREE AN
WON'T GET THAT MONEY.
I UNDERSTAND WHY SOMEONE WANTS
TO GET THEIR MONEY, AND I ALSO
UNDERSTAND WHY HE WANTS TO KEEP
THEM IN SCHOOL FOR AS LONG AS HE
WANTS.
PAPI: I GOT A SIMPLE SOLUTION
FOR TRICKY NICKY.
DAN: WHAT'S THAT?
PAPI: INCREASE THE SALARY FOR
HIS PLAYERS, MAYBE THEY STAY
FOUR OR FIVE MORE YEARS, THAT'S
IT.
DAN: NO, WE DON'T APOLOGIZE FOR
THAT.
♪♪
DAN: COME ON, GONZO, APOLOGIZE
TO NICK SABAN AND ALABAMA FOR
THE HUNDREDTH TIME, MESA.
PAPI: I'M SORRY TO TRICKY NICKY
AND ALABAMA BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW
HOW MUCH THE PLAYERS ARE MAKING.
MAYBE THEY'RE MAKING A LOT MONEY
NOW.
MAYBE THEY DON'T NEED A RAISE,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
MAYBE THEY DON'T NEED TO GO TO
THE NFL, THAT THEY'RE HAPPY WITH
THE MONEY THEY'RE MAKING.
DAN: THAT'S NOT AN APOLOGY.
THAT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE AN
APOLOGY.
PAPI: COMING UP NEXT ON "HIGHLY
QUESTIONABLE" --
>>
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ♪♪
DAN: A CONFETTI POPPER, I'VE HAD
ISSUES WITH THOSE.
PAPI: MY SON'S TV SHOW IS
BROUGHT TO YOU BY T-MOBILE,
WHETHER YOU'RE HOME OR AWAY,
T-MOBILE HAS YOU COVERED.
Almost time for me to go.
, .
drove me home?
What if we lost track of time?
[♪♪]
What if we took a leap of faith?
Whoo-hoo!
What if you...
missed my flight next week?
[♪♪]
The All-New RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
zThe one with the designer dog
collar.
The All-New RAV4.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.■■■rññ■ç
What would she do without me?
♪♪
Every day,
■#■#■#aries are creatinge futur.
♪♪
So, every day,
we put our latest technology
and unrivaork.
♪♪
The United States
Postal Service makes
more e-commerce
deliveries to homes
than anyone else
in the country.
♪♪
Because the future only
happens with people
who really know how
to deliver it.
Because the future only
happens with people
At AutoZone,
we'll help you kiss that check
engine light goodbye.
Our Free Fix Finder service
told him the most likely fix.
And our free Loan-A-Tool
program helped him fix it.
Need a repair shop?
We know some of the best.
Getting the job done
just got easier.
PAPI: FINAL TO PLAY THE GAME
THAT HAS THE BEST SCREAM AT THIS
TABLE, DO YOU QUESTION.
CHRIS: YOU GIVE US TOPICS AND
EVENT AND WE QUESTION THEM.
DAN: HIS SCREAM IS SO MUCH
BETTER THAN YOURS.
PAPI: YEAH?
PAPI: DO YOU QUESTION IF ALEX
CARUSO LET HIS LAST DUNK GET TO
HIS HEAD?
DAN: CHRIS BOSH, HAVVER
SEEN HIM PLAY?
CHRIS: I ACTUALLY HAVE.
DAN: THIS FACE AND THIS FAIR,
HAVE YOU SEEN IT DO --
CHRIS: HEY!
DAN: OKAY.
I'M GOING TO GUESS NO, THAT'S
NOT SOMETHING OFFSEEN HIM DO
BEFORE.
LET'S SEE, DID THIS DUNK GO TO
HIS HEAD AGAINST UTAH?
DID HE TRY IT AGAIN?
>> CARUSO, THERE HE GOES?
DAN: THAT MUSTACHE WENT RIGHT AT
GOBERT.
WHAT IS THAT?
AN.
DAN: HE CAN JUMN JUMP.
GO FOR IT.T WAS CLOSE.
DAN: WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT'S AN OFFENSIVE FOUL.
HE HIT HIM WITH HIS LEFT ELBOW?
CHRIS: MAKES YOU GO HIGHER.
[LAUGHTER]
PAPI: DO YOU QUESTION IF THIS
KID SHOULD BE ASHAMED?
DAN: CHRIS BOSH, DID YOU HAVE
THE NETS BEING PLAYOFF GOOD THIS
YEAR?
YES OR NO.
CHRIS: I DID NOT.
DAN: DID YOU HAVE D'ANGELO
RUSSELL BEING A BREAKOUT
ALL-STAR?
CHRIS: I DID NOT.
DAN: OKAY.
WE HAVE HIM FOR HIS EXPERTISE
AND ABILITY TO FORESEE THE
FUTURE.
LET'S SEE WHAT D'ANGELO RUSSELL
DID IN A PICKUP GAME?
DRESSED FOR A PHOTO SHOOT.
OH, THERE WE GO.
OKAY.
CHRIS: YEAH, THE KID SHOULD BE
ASHAME.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
EVERYBODY THINKS THEY CAN MAY
AGAINST NBA PLAYERS.
YOU CANNOT.
THAT WILL HAPPEN TO YOU.
SO EVERYBODY WATCHING, THESE ARE
THE BEST PLAYERS IN THE WORLD.
HE'S AN ALL-STAR.
DAN: CHRIS BOSH JUST DIDN'T KNOW
IT BEFORE THE SEASON, THAT'S
ALL.
PAPI: YOU KNOW, YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS VERY HARD TO GUARD NBA
PLAYERS.
NO, DON'T DO THIS TO HIM
AGAIN.
COME ON, MAN!
OH, FOR THE LOVE OF GOD.
CHRI">■>">">■>■>■>■>, THOUGH.
HE PUSHED ME.
DAN: HE PUSH HIM.■>■■■v■p■÷OVE!
HE'S BG THAT FOR 40
YEARS.
CHRIS: AND WHO'S THAT BY ME?
MY MAN, K.D.
THAT'S WHY YOU MY GUY.
DAN: THAT'S RIGHT.
PAPI: DO YOU QUESTION IF ONLY A
FOOL WOULD MAKE THIS MISTAKE?
DAN: OKAY.
WE'RE GOING ANALYZE HOW FOOLISH
THIS HERE.
THAT'S WHY WE BROUGHT HIM IN
HERE.
HE'S HEADED TO THE HALL OF FAME.
THIS IS A FATHER CELEBRATING HIS
SON'S BIRTHDAY.
♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ♪♪
DAN: OH, A CONFETTI POPPER.
I'VE HAD ISSUES WITH THOSE.
>> OH, NO.
DAN: IS HE GOING TO HIT HIM IN
THE FACE?
OH!
OH, HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
CHRIS: GIVE THE DUDE SOME
CREDIT, THOUGH, HE GAVE HIS SON
SOMETHING HE WILL NEVER FORGET.
DAN: YES, BUZZ WILLIAMS' SON
WILL NEVER FORGET.
CHRIS: WAY TO GO, DAD.
PAPI: HASTEN IDIOT CAN'T WORK A
CONFETTI POPPER?
I was tired
of having my calls dropped,
and then I'd heard that I could
get Apple Music
if I switched over
and I said, "BOOM!"
(VO)
The best network is even better
with Apple Music
on us.
Plus save big when you switch.
Only on Verizon.
■■8é=é=é=é=zz■■8M>8■.Ñ/■■=■=■=■■
Some say we're a little
spoiled in California.
But it isn't OUR faux1
We're in awe, too.
Woo!
We get a little star-struck.
Did you see who's here?
What?
Come visit!
It might take your breath
away, too!
St trip at
visitcalifornia.com
♪ LiMu Emu & Doug ♪
What do all these people
have in common, Limu?
[ paper rustling ]
Exactly, nothing.
They're completely
different people,
that's why they
need customized
Car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need!
[ gargling ]
[ coins hitting the desk ]
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done
it again, LiMu.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
■■■>■>■>■>■8■>■8■8■8■>■>■>■>■■>■
Not much here,
ethbit?the usual.GGGGGGGe
Alexa...
"Fire"
by The Ohio Players
♪Fire (uh) (uh)♪
What if we turn it up a notch?
♪Fire (It's all about) (Uh, uh)♪
What if we go off the map?
♪Fire (Woo, woo, woo)♪
♪Fire♪
The all-new RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
■2
I was tired
of having my calls dropped,
and then I'd heard that I could
get Apple Music
if I switched over
and I said, "BOOM!"
(VO)
The best network is even better
with Apple Music
on us.
Plus save big when you switch.
Only on Verizon.
So...
you're driven,
and you have a ton
of goals...
but you're stuck
in the vicious cycle
of credit card payments.
It's time to get
a personal loan from SoFi.
Borrow up to $100k to
pay off your credit cards,
and then pay us back with
one monthly payment.
And it's all with zero fees.
Get a personal loan,
and pay no fees.
( ♪♪ )
>> YES, YES!
I GOT TO CALL MY DAD!
I'M SO EXCITED ABOUT THIS.
DAN: "HIGHLY QUESTIONABLE" IS
BROADCAST IN THE CLEVELANDER
HOTEL ON BEAUTIFUL SOUTH BEACH
MIAMI.
TIME TO PLAY THE GAME THAT IS
FINALLY HOSTING WITH SOMEONE
THAT HE RESPECTS, SI OR NO.
DAN: THAT'S NOT COOL, MAN.
YOU TELL US WHAT TO WATCH ON
TELEVISION TONIGHT.
WE'LL TELL YOU IF WE'RE
INTRIGUED.
PRODUCER: RIGHT NOW ON AT&T
PITTSBURGH, PIRATES AND CUBS.
DAN: ARE THEY THROWING BASEBALLS
AT EACH OTHER AGAIN?
■■ FOR T■2■2■> REDS PUMPS OUT
A HOME RUN TROT.
WATCHES THE BALL FLY OUT
BIT.■z
YEAH, HE ENJOYED THAT.
LOOK AT HIM, HE'S SMOLDERING AND
BEAUTIFUL, AND OF COURSE HE
SHOULD ENJOY THAT WHEN HE HITS
THE BALL THAT FAR.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS THE NEXT
TIME HE COMES UP.
CHRIS ARCHER SAYS HOW ABOUT SOME
OF THAT RIGHT BEHIND YOU
DIETRICH ISN'T SURPRISED BY IT.
YASIEL PUIG IS A BIG FAN OF
ANYONE ENJOYING THEIR HOME RUN.
HE COMES OUT AND HE WANTS TO
FIGHT EVERY SINGLE PITTSBURGH
PIRATE IN THE ORGANIZATION SINCE
1910, INCLUDING HONUS WAGNER.M■@
EL PUIG?
HE'S IN THE MIDDLE OF
EVERYT
THEN HIS CATNDS UP HERE,
FF VAN GUNDY AROUND ALONZO
MOURNING SHIN SITUATION.
YES, THERE IT IS.
A LOT OF FUN.
NOT A REAL FIGHT.
HOW ABOUT YOU, CHRIS, ARE YOU
INTRIGUED?
CHRIS: SURE, WHY NOT.
I WANT TO SEE IF HE'S GO
AT IT LONGER NEXT TIME.
DAN: YES.
THAT'S WHAT YOU NEED TO DO, HIT
IT LONGER AND LOOK LONGER.
PAPI ARE YOU INTRIGUED?
PAPI: SI, SI.
YASIEL PUIG IS NOW WITH THE
REDS?
DAN: YES.
A LOT OF THAT HAS HAPPENED EARLY
IN THE SEASON.
JOSH DONALDSON IS A BRAVE.
HE IS.
PAPI: YEAH.
PRODUCER: ON MASN 2, A'S AND
ORIOLES.
DAN: CHRIS DAVIS HAS GONE
0 FOR 44 DATING BACK TO LAST
SEASON, 35% OF THE TIME HE'S
STRIKING OUT.
THE ORIOLES GAVE HIM $■■■■■■■■■.
JUST TOTALLY LOST.
THEY BOO HIM.
THAT'S NOT EVEN CLOSE.
IT'S HARD TO WATCH.
THEY'RE BOOING THAT CONTACT AS
MUCH AS ANYTHING.
CHRIS BOSH, ARE YOU INTRIGUED?
CHRIS: I'M NOT INTRIGUED.
I DON'T SEE TO SEE A GUY GO
THROUGH THIS STUFF.
IT'S HARD ENOUGH, BUT 0 FOR 44,
I DON'T WANT TO WATCH A MAN IN
HIS MISERY.
DAN: I KNOW, RIGHT?
PAPI, ARE YOU INTRIGUED?
PAPI: SI, SI.
0 FOR 44, THAT BRINGS BACK OLD
MEMORIES.
THAT SOUND LIKE YOU IN LITTLE
LEAGUE.
YOU WERE ABOUT 0 FOR 63 ONE
TIME.
DAN: 0 FOR 63 ONE TIME.
WASN'T THAT BAD WHE■÷
CONSIDER I WAS&÷ JUST GETTING
STARTED ON MY 0 FOR 63.
PAPI: THAT WASN'T THAT BAD, YOU
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
HE'S DOING GOOD, HE'S DOING
GOOD.
PRODUCER: ON YOUTUBE, CHRIS
BOSH'S PROMOTIONAL VIDEO FOR THE
2008 ALL-STAR GAME.
DAN: YES, I WANT TO SEE THIS!
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT CHRIS BOSH
BACK THEN WHEN HE WANTS TO BE IN
THE ALL-STAR GAME.
>> 'TIS THE SEASON.
THIS IS CHRIS BOSH HERE,
OFFERING YOU A POST-CHRISTMAS
SERB, A NEW YEAR'S=>CIAL.
BRING THE 2008 YEAR IN RIGHT.
VOTE FOR ME.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, GET AN
ALL-STAR BALLOT RIGHT NOW AND
PUNCH IN MY NAME.
DAN: YOU WERE REALLY SKINNY.
CHRIS: I WAS GOING FOR IT, MAN.
>> WE DON'T WANT YOUR MONEY
HERE.
WE JUST WANT YOUR VOTE.
TIME IS ALMOST UP.
THESE THINGS ARE MOVING FAST.
GET ONE OF THESE BATTLE, PUNCH
IN MY NAME.
OR GO TO NBA.COM.
OR BETTER YET GO TO MY WEBSITE
AN VOTE FOR ME TODAY.
SEE YOU IN NEW ORLEANS.
DAN: IS THAT SHIRT BAGGY OR YOU
GOT A POTBELLY?
WHY DID YOU TAKE OUT POOR
BUBBA'S TEETH?
CHRIS, ARE YOU INTRIGUED?
CHRIS: ALWAYS.
CLASSIC.
DAN: FIRST I DISCOVERED HE WAS
FUNNY WAS RIGHT THERE IN THOSE
VIDEOS.
PAPI, ARE YOU INTRIGUED?
PAPI: SI, SI.
THIS BRINGS BACK OLE MEMORIES.
REMEMBER, WHEN YOU DIDN'T MAKE
THE ALL-STAR TEAM IN LITTLE
LEAGUE BECAUSE YOU WERE MISSING
ONE VOTE.
DAN: I DID.
PAPI: THAT'S RIGHT.
ONE VOTING YOU WERE MISSING.
DAN: TRUE STORY.
HIS VOTE.
HE WAS THE COACH.
YOU THINK I'M JOKING.
I'M NOT JOKING.
BY ONE VOTE, I MIFF THE ALL-STAR
TEAM.
MY FATHER WAS THE COACH.
TRUE STORY.
PAPI: I DIDN'T GIVE YOU MY VOTE.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S ALL THE TIME WE HAVE FOR
TODAY.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
DAN: OUR THANKS AGAIN TO CHRIS
BOSH FOR BEING SUCH A GOOD
SPORT.
FOLLOW HIM IN ALL THE PLACES YOU
COULD FOLLOW CHRIS BOSH.
PAPI: WHERE'S THE WATER?
CAN I HAVE A SIP OF YOUR WATER?
DAN: OH, CHRIS.
PAPI: I GOT HIM AGAIN!
DAN: PAPI, WHY DID YOU DO THAT
TO HIM?
PAPI!