SO I GET IT.
AND SOMETIMES I WATCH HIM FROM
PLAY TO PLAY AND BE LIKE, BEST
PLAYER EVER.
AND THE VERY NEXT PLAY I THINK,
YOU CAN'T WIN A CHAMPIONSHIP
WITH THIS GUY.
I WANT THE SWINGS.
HE IS THE TYPE OF DUDE THAT
COULD BE VOTED MOST UNDERRATED
AND OVERRATED IN THE SAME POLL.
HE IS THAT KIND OF PLAYER.
MOLLY: HOW ABOUT THIS, GUYS?
WE ASKED EVERYONE AT HOME DOES
AARON RODGERS HAVE SOMETHING HE
NEEDS TO PROVE NEXT SEASON?
STEPHEN A. SMITH, PERK UP YOUR
EARS.
72% SAID YES.
THEY ACTUALLYD ABSOLUTELY
[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
ESPN, INC.]
>> COIPT MASTERS PAIRINGS ARE
OUT.
LIVE IN AUGUSTA WITH WHO TIGER
WILL BE PLAYING WITH THURSDAY
AND FRIDAY.
THE CAVALIERS' RIDE TO
REDEMPTION, WE'RE LIVE IN
CHARLOTTESVILLE AS VIRGINIA
CELEBRATES.
PLUS WE ALSO LOOK BACK AT A
MUSIC ICON' BASKETBALL CAREER.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT PRINCE. ■■'.
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTIONING CONTENT AND
ACCURACY. VISIT NCICAP.ORG]
>> YOU ARE WEARING A BLOUSE.
>> A SHIRT WITH RUFFLES, CHRIS.
CARI: AHAD YOU, A SHIRT WITH
RUFFLES.
JAY, I HOPE THAT -- YOU DON'T
HAVE YOUR SHIRT WITH RUFFLES.
JAY: NO, I LEFT IT HOME TODAY.
VERDICT WORN IT.
CARI: DAVID LLOYD IS ON
VACATION, TRAVELING THE WORLD,
WHO KNOWS.
MEANWHILE, LET'S GET RIGHT TO
IT.
JAY, DID YOU HAVE VIRGINIA
WINNING IT ALL?
JAY: NO, I DID NOT.
I PICKED DUKE.
DAVID LLOYD DID PICK VIRGINIA,
AND HE WON OUR INTERNAL BRACKET
CHALLENGE.
CONGRATS TO HIM.
HERE'S HOW AND HE VIRGINIA
IT ALL.
THEY HAD A GOOD NIGHT.
NUMBER ONE VIRGINIA TECH AND
THREE SEED TEXAS TEC
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
PICK IT UP SECOND HALF,
VIRGINIA DOWN THREE, UNDER 20
SECONDS TO GO.
THEY'VE BEEN DOWN THE LAST FEW
GAMES,■)w%T DOESN'T MATT
TO THEM.
TY■■[■I TO DE'ANDMENTOW YOU GOIç
CROWD GOING
VIRGINIA. ■,íFING TEXAS TECH PO
JARRETT CULVER, THREE-POINT
JUMPER, NO.
HUNTER GETS THE REBOUND.
TRIES TO KICK  OUT, BUT IT
UT OF BOUNDS.
ALL RIGHT.
CHECK OUT KYLE GUY, TRIES TO
CALL TIME-OUT, AND HUNTER TRIES
TO PASS TO GUY AT THE SAME
TIME, SO THEY LOSE IT.
COSTLY TURNOVER.P■ TECH WI■NCE
SECOND LEFT.
AND NO.
THE SHOCK WAS BLOCKED.
WE G OVERTIME.
FIRST O.T. IN A NATIONAL TITLE
GAME■■■■ SINCE
HUNTER, THAT CORNER AGAIN.
27 POINTS IN THIS ONE, 22 IN
THE SECOND HALF AND OVERTIME.
THE VIRGINIA FANS ARE GOING
CRAZY.
1:15e■e■e■ TO PLAY.
JEROME DRIVING.o■■/qvñ■■Ph■
NO.
LONG REBOUND.
CROSSIDCOURT.
WE'VE SEEN THAT BEFORE, BUT
TECH GETS IT, AND OH, HUNTER
POKES IT A AFTER MORETTI
CHASES IT DOWN.
THE CALL ON THE FLOOR, TEXAS
TECH BALL.
THEY REVIEWED IT.
LOOKS LIKE LAST TOUCHEDB BY
MORETTI.
CALL OVERTURNED.
U.V.A. BALL.
AND TEXAS TECH FORCED TO FOUL,
AND JEROME, THE LONG PASS AND
THE DUNK, AND VIRGINIA WINS,
AND THEY'RE GOING CRAZY.
THE FIRST-EVER NATIONAL TITLE ■
I'M JUST THINKING THIS IS A
DREAM COME TRUFMENTE
>> YOU HAVE SCARS, RIGHT?
YOU HAVE A SCAR THAT REMINDS
YOU OF THAT, BUT, YOU KNOW,
LITTLE A MEMORY, AND DOES IT GO
AWAY COMPLETE?
NO, I WISH IT WOULDN'T HAVE
HAPPENED.
BUT NOW, IT BOUGHT US A TICKET
HERE, SO BE IT.
>> I THINK THE MOST IMPORTANT
PART, RIGHT AFTER THAT GAME, WE
ALL REACTED, AND INSTEAD OF,
YOU KNOW, WE DEFINITELY HAD OUR
TIME WHERE WE WERE IN OUR
SHELLS AND UPSET AND WHATNOT.
BUT TO BE ABLE TO MOVE PAST
THAT AND GET WHERE WE ARE RIGHT
NOW IS INCREDIBLE.
>> CHRIS, LOOKED LIKE YOU
STOPPED TO TALK TO A COUPLE OF
YOUR GUYS BEFORE THEY WALK OFF
THE FLOOR.
WHAT WAS YOUR MESSAGE TO THEM
AFTER THE GAME THERE?
>> JUST -- MAN, WHEW.
JUST TOLD THEM I LOVED THEM.
YOU KNOW, OUR RELATIONSHIP IS
JUST GETTING STARTED.
I'LL BE WITH THOSE GUYS AT
THEIR WEDDINGS ONE DAY, AND
HOPEFUL WHEN WILL THEIR KIDS
GET BORN.
DO EVERYTHING I CAN TO TALK
THEM OUT OF GETTING INTO
COACHING SO THEY DON'T EVER
FEEL LIKE THIS.
YOU KNOW, I JUST LOVE THOSE
GUYS.
JAY: WELL, DEFENSE WINS
CHAMPIONSHIPS, AND VIRGINIA IS
THE FIRST TEAM SINCE THE
1958-1959 CAL BEARS TO LEAD
DIVISION I IN SCORING, DEFENSE,
AND WIN THE TITLE.
VIRGINIA ONLY ALLOWED THEIR
OPPONENTS TO SCORE JUST NORTH
OF 56 POINTS PER GAME, WHICH IS
THE LOWEST SINCE, WELL, LAST
YEAR, WHEN THE CAVALIERS HELD
OPPONENTS TO 54 POINTS PER
GAME.
A CELEBRATION, AS YOU CAN SEE.
THIS WAS THE SCENE
■kARLOTTESVILLE AS THEY
BASKETBALL TITLE IN SCHOOL
HISTORY.
CO■HAT.
THOUSANDS OF STUDENTS
CELEBRATED AS THEY WATCHED THE
GAME THERE IN THE ARENA, AND
THEN THERE WERE THOSE W LIN
STREETS OF THAT CITY.
SO, IS THERE■W STILL A
CELEBRATION ON CAMPUS?
THAT IS THE QUESTION.
WE ARE NOW JOINED BY COLLEGE
SPORTS REPORTER, ED ASCHOFF
FROM VIRGINIA.
THE CHAMPIONS WILL BE HOME
SOMETIME TODAY.
CAN YOU SET THE SCENE FOR THE
FEEL CAMPUS, AND WHAT HAPPENS
NEXT AS THE CHAMPIONS PREPARE
FOR THE CELEBRATION?
ED: CARI, AS YOU CAN SEE BEHIND
ME, THE MOOD IS A LITTLE BIT
MORE SUBDUED NOW COMPARED TO
LAST NIGHT'S CELEBRATION AT THE
CORNER.
BUT I WOULD SAY THAT THE
BIGGEST THINGS THAT I'VE HEARD
FROM FANS, UTTER JOY AND UTTER
JUST PEACE OF BEING VIRGINIA
FANS, CONSIDERING EVERYTHING
THAT HAS HAPPENED TO THIS
PROGRAM.
LOSING TO A 16 SEED LAST YEAR
AS A ONE SEED.
I TALKED TO A WOMAN LAST NIGHT
WHO TOLD ME, LOOK, I JUST GOT A
TEXT MESSAGE FROM A FRIEND WHO
TOLD ME, REGARDLESS OF THE
GENDER OF THE BABY I'M GOING TO
HAVE, I'M NAMING THAT CHILD
AFTER TONY BENNETT.
EARLIER, RIGHT BEFORE WE CAME
ON AIR, WE HEARD A WOMAN IN HER
CAR BLASTING QUEEN'S "WE ARE
THE CHAMPIONS," POINTING AT US
AND SINGING.
A GUY LAST NIGHT TOLD ME HE WAS
JUST SO RELIEVED, BECAUSE HE'S
BEEN AT THIS UNIVERSITY FOR SO
LONG.
HE LOOKED AT ME AND JUST SAID,
10 YEARS WITH TONY BENNETT.
FINALLY WE HAVE A CHAMPIONSHIP.
AND I'LL SAY THIS, IT WAS
PRETTY RAUCOUS LAST NIGHT, BUT
A GUY AT CONVENIENCE STORE TOLD
ME THIS CELEBRATION WASN'T
CLOSE TO BEING AS CRAZY AS IT
WAS SATURDAY AFTER THEY BEAT
AUBURN TO GET TO THE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP.
SO I THINK THAT THERE'S SO MUCH
RELIEF HERE, THERE'S SO MUCH
EXCITEMENT, BUT THEY ARE JUST
SO HAPPY TO FINALLY SEE A
CHAMPIONSHIP IN
CHARLOTTESVILLE.
CARI: WE GOT ONE PARTIER BEHIND
US GIVING YOU A HIGH FIVE IN
THE BACKGROUND.
ED: THERE YOU GO.
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
CARI: THAT IS OUR ED ASCHOFF.
ODDS ARE OUT FOR NEXT YEAR, AND
OUR FRIENDS AT WASTE GATE GIVE
VIRGINIA A GOOD CHANCE TO
REPEAT.
THEY ARE TIED WITH KENTUCKY FOR
THE BEST ODDS TO WIN THE TITLE.
THEY'RE FOLLOWED BY DUKE AND
MICHIGAN STATE AT 8-1.
AND MICHIGAN WOLVERINES ROUND
OUT THE TOP FIVE AT 12-1.
JAY: CARI, COLLEGE HOOPS IS
SO IT IS TIME WE TURN OUR
ATTENTION TO THE MASTERS.
TIGER WOODS GOT SOME PRACTICE
IN YESTERDAY AT AUGUSTA BEFORE
SEVERE WEATHER CAME IN MID
AFTERNOON AND SUSPENDED PLAY.
MASTERS STARTS THURSDAY.
TIGER WITH FOUR GREEN JACKETS,
AMONG THE BETTING FAVORITES AND
EMOTIONAL FAVORITES TO WIN HIS
FIFTH GREEN JACKET AND HIS 15TH
MAJOR.
TIME FOR US TO HEAD TO AUGUSTA
NATIONAL■ ROW.
MASTERS. ONTINUE FOR THE
NORTH ANCHORING OUROVERAGE.
TUESDAY TO YOU, GENTLEMEN.
>> GOOD TU YOU■ AS WELL
JAY.
YES, WEATHER STILL AN ISSUE HER.
■ x x ■■PEOR THE■
THET@ GOLF COURSE.■■■■■F■F@
THE INTERRUPTION OF THE
■@@@ O■
PLAYERS ISS
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT IN A
MOMENT.
BUT WE DO HAVE SOME NEWS NEAR
AUGUSTA NATIONAL.
GROUPING FOR THE FIRST ROUND
HAVE BEEN RELEASED.
LET'S STARTS WITH 11:04 A.M.
TIGER WOODS GOING OUT WITH LEE
AND JON RAHM.
ANDY: OBVIOUSLY TIGER HAS
PLAYED REALLY GOOD GOLF.
HIS PUTTING HASN'T BEEN UP TO
SNUFMENT HE'S GOT TO PUTT
BETTER THIS WEEK.
I THINK HE WILL.
BUT JON RAHM, HERE'S A PLAYER
THAT I THINK EVERY TIME HE
WALKS ON THIS GOLF COURSE FROM
NOW UNTIL HE FINISHES PLAYING H.
MICHAEL: VERY MUCH SO.
BEHIND THEM, REMEMBER TRYING
COMPLETE THE CAREER GRAND SLAM.
ANDY: COULD YOU SAY, WOULD YOU
THAT I GROUP AGAINST THE REST
OF THE FIELD?
YOU MIGHT DO THAT.
RORY IS PLAYING BEAUTIFULLY.
WILL HE PUTT WELL ENOUGH TO
WIN?
HE'S HAD CHANCES BEFORE, THE
WAY HE DRIVES THE BALL, HE IS
THE FAVORITE TO WIN.
RICKIE PLAYS WELL.
CA SMITH, PLAYED WELL LAST
YEAR.
MICHAEL: IN THE AFTERNOON, TWO
FORMER WINNERS IN JASON DAY AND
JUSTIN JOHNSON.
BRYSON DECHAMBEAU LOOKING FOR
THE FIRST MAJOR.
ANDY: DUSTIN JOHNSON'S STYLE
FITS IT BETTER THAN ALMOST
ANYBODY.
THE WAY HE DRIVES THE BALL, HIS
PUTTING, AGAIN, HE'S A LITTLE
BID COLD WITH IT.
BUT IF HE'S GOOD, HE'S REALLY
GOOD.
MICHAEL: YOU GOT PHIL MICKELSON
GOING OFF WITH JUSTIN ROSE AND
JUSTIN THOMAS.
ANDY: JUSTIN ROSE QUIETLY THE
NUMBER ONE PLAYER IN THE WORLD.
BUT IF YOU DID "WHICH JUSTIN
WOULD YOU TAKE," I LOVE JUSTIN
THOMAS F. YONG BET ON
HIM OVER THE NEXT 10 YEARS,
HE'S GOING TO WIN MULTIPLE
MAJOR CHAMPIONSHIPS.
PHIL, EVERY TIME HE DRIVES IN
HERE, HE THINKS HE CAN WIN.
MICHAEL: THREE-TIME WINNER HERE
AT THE MASTERS.
JORDAN SPIETH LOOKING TO GET
HIS GAME IN ORDER AGAIN, MAYBE
WIN A SECOND GREEN JACKET.
HE WILL PLAY WITH PAUL CASEY
AND BROOKS KOEPKA.
ANDY: ALL THE SUDDEN BROOKS
KOEPKA IS PLAYING GREAT GOLF.
HE HASN'T PLAYED THAT YET ON
THIS COURSE, BUT IT FITS HIS
GAMEERFECTLY.
JORDAN SPIETH HAS PLAYED BETTER
HERE THE LAST FIVE YEARS VERSUS
ANYBODY.
MICHAEL: BROOKS KOEPKA DID NOT
PLAY HERE LAST YEAR DUE TO
INJURY.
IT'S ONE THING TO PICK SOMEBODY
YOU THINK IS GOING PLAY WELL,
AND THEN YOU SEE THE GROUPING.
HOW DOES THAT AFFECT YOUR
MINDSET IN WHO YOU LIKE TO WIN?
ANDY: THESE GUYS ALL PLAY WITH
EACH OTHER, OR GET PAIRED WITH
EACH OTHER, EVERY TIME THEY
PLAY GOLF.
THAT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
I THINK THE KEY IS THAT THEY'RE
ALL GOING TO BE IN OUR COVERAGE
LATE THURSDAY AND LATE FRIDAY,
AND THAT'S THE REAL KEY.
THEY'RE GOING TO BE RIGHT IN
THE MIDDLE OF THIS.
THEY'RE ALL PLAYING REALLY
WELL.
THIS GOLF COURSE FITS THEIR
GAMES, SO MANY OF THEIR GAMES
REALLY WELL.
I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE AN
AMAZING THURSDAY AND FRIDAY OF
GOLF.
MICHAEL: AS YOU SEE BEHIND US,
THE PRACTICE AREA HERE CLOSED.
HOW IS THE WEATHER AFFECTING
PREPARATION?
FOR MORE ON THAT, LET'S BRING
IN OUR GOOD FRIEND, GENE ADRIAN
WOJNAROWSKI.
-- GENE WOJCIECHOWSKI.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
GENE: IF YOU LOOK AT THE
WEATHER CHANNEL RADAR THESE
DAYS, THOSE ARE THE TWO
DOMINANT COLORS YOU'RE GOING TO
SEE ON THE SCREEN, GREEN AND
YELLOW.
APPEARS THE RAINS MOVE THROUGH,
RICKIE FOWLER NORMALLY WOULDN'T
PLAY ON A MONDAY, BUT HE
DECIDED, AFTER LOOKING AT THE
FORECAST, TO COME OUT HERE.
HE PLAYED NINE HOLES BECAUSE HE
SAW TUESDAY WOULD BE IFFY.
AND THEN THERE'S TIGER WOODS,
WHO HOPED TO PLAY NINE HOLES
BEFORE OR AFTER HIS 1:00 P.M.
PRESS CONFERENCE TODAY.
NOW HE MIGHT BE ABLE TO PLAY
SOME HOLES, MAYBE AT LEAST GET
OUT TO THE RANGE AND HIT SOME
BALLS.
THEN THERE'S BROOKS KOEPKA, WHO
WE JUST SAW ON THE LIST.
NOTHING FAZESIM.
I'M NOT EVEN SURE HE HAS A
PULSE.
HE SAID IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT
THE RAINS DO TO THE
PREPARATION.
HE REMINDED ALL OF US IN
PRESS CONFERENCE THIS MORNING
THAT AT THE PGA CHAMPIONSHIP
LAST YEAR, WELL, IT RAINED ON
TUESDAY.
IT RAINED AGAIN ON FRIDAY.
AND&GUESS WHO WON THAT
TOURNAMENT AND THAT MAJOR.
BROOKS KOEPKA, MICHAEL.
MICHAEL: LOOKING TO GET HIS
FIRST GREEN JACKET IF HE CAN
HAVE THAT HISTORY REPEAT.
COMING UP HERE, COMING UP TOP
OF THE HOUR ON ESPN2, YOU WILL
HEAR FROM TIGER WOODS, HIS NEWS
CONFERENCE HERE AT AUGUSTA
NATIONAL.
THEN 2:30 OVER ON ESPNE
PHIL MICKELSON, FOLLOWED BY
RORY MCILROY. ■■■■Ñ■■■)■)o ■p■@
SPIETH.
OF COURSE, LOOKING FOR HIS
SECOND GREEN JACKET.
AND DUSTIN JOHNSON, YOU WILL
SEE HIM AT 4:00 P.M. EASTERN ON
ESPNEWS.
PLENTY MORE COVERAGE THROUGHOUT
THE DAY HERE FROM AUGUSTA
NATIONAL.
FOR NOW, BACK TO
"SPORTSCENTER."
JAY: MICHAEL, TOMORROW WE
ALWAYS LOOK FORWARD TO THIS FUN
AND FAMILY-ORIENTED TRADITION
T. STARTED IN 1960, THE MASTERS
PAR 3 CONTEST FROM AUGUSTA.
3:00 P.M. EASTERN, ESPN AND THE
ESPN APP.
SO YOU CAN WATCH AT WORK OR
WHEREVER YOU MAY BE, CARI.
CARI: JAY, FOLKS ATOME,
COMING UER A
SEASON-ENDING IN MISERY
ASKE■ J t&■R LAKER■@■@Sg GREAT,
WHAT'S THE MISSING PIECE FOR
SUCCESS?
PLUS, TODD PLAYS G.M.
WITH THEEVEAL OF■F HIS GRADE
A'S.
:=■=
Hmm. Exactly.
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay
for what you need.
Nice. But, uh...
what's up with
your... partner?
Not again. LiMu
that's your reflection.
Only pu need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
♪ ♪
Plants capture CO2.
What if other kinds óó■■■■■?■18
If these industrial plants had
techno■=■=■=■=■=Ñ;■;■
that captured carbon like trees
we could help lower emissions.
Carbon Capture is important
technology -
and experts agree.
That's why we're working on ways
to improve it.
So plants...
can be a little more...
like plants.
♪ ♪
■■,■■■■8
I'm just a normal person who
got an awful skin condition.
With uncontrolled
moderate-to-severe eczema,
or atopic dermatitis...
...you feel like you're
itching all the time.
And you never know
how your skin will look.
Because de■thin your .
...an overly sensitive immune
system...
...could be the cause.
So help heal your skin from
within.
With DUPIXENT.
DUPIXENT is not a steroid,...
...and it continuously treats
your eczema...
...even when you can't see it.
At 16 weeks, nearly four times
more patients
taking DUPIXENT saw clear or
almost clear skin
compared to those not taking
it.
...and patients saw a
significant reduction in itch.
Do not use if you are allergic
to DUPIXENT.
Serious allergic reactions can
occur,
including anaphylaxis, a
severe reaction.
Tell your doctor if you have
new or worsening eye problems,
including eye pain or changes
in vision.
If you are taking asthma
medicines,
do not change or stop your
asthma medicine
without talking to your doctor.
Help heal your skin from
within.
Ask your eczema specialist
about DUPIXENT.
With Graññ
that will lead you to somewhere
unexpected.tional
Somewhere you can create
something...
better than good.
Here, you'll create something
grand.
Grand Marnier.
A visionary blend of fine cognac
and bitter orange liqueur.
Live Grand.
We got no free pass.
Everything we have,
we've earned.
The unmistakable Lexus IS.
Lease the 2019 IS 300 for
$329 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
I had no symptoms
of Hepatitis C.
Mine...
...caused liver damage.
EPCLUSA treats all main types
of chronic Hep C.
Whatever your type,
ask your doctor
if EPCLUSA is your kind of cure.
I had the common type.
Mine was rare.
EPCLUSA has a 98%
overall cure rate.
I just found out
about my hepatitis C.
I knew for years.
EPCLUSA is only one
food for 12 weeks.aken wt
Before starting EPCLUSA,
your doctor will
test if you have had
hepatitis B, which may flare up
and could cause
serious liver problems
during and after treatment.
Tell your doctor if you
have had hepatitis B
other liver or
kidney problems, HIV
or other medical conditions...%
...and a=es you take,
including herbal supplements.
Taking amiodarone
with EPCLUSA may
cause a serious slowing
of your heart rate.
Common side effects include
headache and tiredness
Ask your doctor today, if
EPCLUSA is your kind of cure.
>> "SPORTSCENTER" IS BROUGHT TO
YOU BY "HELLBOY," ONE HELL OF A
SUPERHERO, IN THEATERS FRIDAY.
JAY: BACK ON "SPORTSCENTER,"
CARI CHAMPION, JAY HARRIS.
PLAYOFF PICT THE NBA'S
EASTERN CONFERENCE, PISTONS
CURRENTLY IN THE EIGHTH SPOT, A
GAME AHEAD OF BOTH HORNETS AND
HEAT.
THEY CONTROL THEIR OWN DESTINY
WITH TWO GAMES TO GO IN THEIR
SCHEDULE.
THE HORNETS RIGHT NOWUPY
THE NINTH SEED, AND
GET INTO T PLAYOFFS, THEY
NEED TOITHER TIE■■& PASS THE
PISTONSINCEROIT
ALES THIS YEAR AND
OWN THE TIEBREA■n■
AND ■■p
ç@ ARE TIED WITH THETS4>TW;'T H
WHICH MAKES THEIR CHANCES OF
PRETTY SLIM.
B.P.I. ONLY GIVES THEMG7 1%
CHANCE TO MAKE IT, WHICH MEANS
WE ONLY HAVE TWO MORE GAMES TO
WATCH D. WADE.
CARI: AND THAT IS A BUMMER.
MEANWHILE, FROM THE BOTTOM OF
THE EAST PLAYOFF PICTURE, WE GO
TO THE BOTTOM OF THE WEST.
THUNDER-SPURS.
CLIPPERS FIGHTING FOR SEEDING,
AND THEY ARE ALL SEPARATED BY
JUST HALF A GAME.
IT'S TOUGH OUT HERE.
THESE TEAMS STILL HAVE A LOT TO
PLAY FOR IN ORDER TO AVOID
BEING THE EIGHT SEED AND FACE
THE WARRIORS IN THE FIRST
ROUND.
NO ONE WANTS THE CHAMPS.
SPEAKING OF THE WEST, FORMER
LAKER GREAT RICK FOX JOINS ME
NOW RIGHT NOW ON "COAST TO
COAST."
SUCH A PLEASURE TO HAVE YOU
HERE.
YOU HAVE THREE CHAMPIONSHIPS
WITH THE LAKERS.
WE OBJECT -- OBVIOUS HAVE THE
TO START THERE.
I WANT TO ASK YOU QUITE SIMPLY,
IN YOUR OPINION, WHAT WENT
WRONG?
RICK: HEALTH.
HEALTH.
I LOOK BACK AT THE CHRISTMAS
DAY GAME, AND I KNOW OF
LEBRON'S INJURY.
MOMENTUM WAS BUILDING.
AND THEN HE WAS DOWN.
HE WAS DOWN FOR A NUMBER OF
MONTHS.
WHEN HE RETURNED, I THINK THE
TRADE DEADLINE ALSO THEN
CREATED A SITUATION FOR OUR
YOUNG PLAYERS TO EXPERIENCE
WHAT IT MEANS TO BE AN NBA
PLAYER PROFESSIONALLY AND
BUSINESS-WISE.
SOME OFM HANDLED IT WELL,■@
OTHERS DIDN'T.
D I THINK@d■  AOINT, I
THINK THEOO STRONG,
AND WE SPIRALED OUT.
CARI: THE■ WEST IS VERY STRO
I YOU GAVE SOMELLY
GOOD REASONS.
HEALTH IS ONE OF THESE THINGS
THAT PEOPLE DON'T TALK ABOUT
WHEN IT COMES TO THE LAKERS.
IT'S MORE ABOUT THE DRAMA.
YOU TALK ABOUT THE A.D.
SITUATION IN TERMS OF THE TRADE
DEADLINE, BUT THE OTHER DRAMA
IS LUKE WALTON.
LET'S STAY RIGHT THERE.
CAN YOU EXPLAIN WHY THERE ARE
SO MANY RUMORS AND PERHAPS
EXPECTATIONS THAT LUKE WALTON
WILL LOSE HIS JOB?
RICK: I THINK IT'S BECAUSE OF
THE EXPECTATIONS.
THIS IS LOS ANGELES.
WE UNDERSTAND THE LEVEL OF
EXCELLENCE THAT IS EXPECTED
FROM THE FANS AND EXPECTED FROM
THE ORGANIZATION.
WE CHASE CHAMPIONSHIPS, AND
WE'VE FALLEN SHORT.
I THINK THE IMPROVEMENT MAY BE
THERE IN THE PLAYERS, IF YOU
LOOK AT LUKE'S JOB, WHEN IT
COMES TO NURTURING THOSE GUYS
AND GROWING THEM.
BUT RIGHT NOW, IT'S ABOUT BEING
IN THE PLAYOFFS AND CHASING A
CHAMPIONSHIP.
WE'VE FALLEN SHORT AGAIN.
I UNDERSTAND THE EXPECTATIONS
THAT COME WITH A COACH AND
BEING JUDGED AT THE END OF THE
SEASON, AND IT STARTS WITH THAT
COACH PROBABLY.
CARI: IS IT FAIR?
THAT'S A YES OR NO.
RICK: I DON'T THINK IT'S --
LIFE'S NOT FAIR.
I'LL GO THERE.
CARI: WELL, THERE YOU GO.
THAT IS THE ANSWER.
FOLKS, YOU CAN HEAR AND SEE
MORE OF RICK FOX ON MORNING
SHOW "MYSTERIES," A MURDER IN
MIND PREMIERING THIS SUNDAY ON
HALLMARK MOVIES AND MYSTERIES.
RICK FOX, I APPRECIATE YOUR
TIME AND JOINING US ON "COAST
TO COAST."
RICK: GOOD TO SEE YOU.
JAY: CARI, RICK, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT TODD MCSHAY'S
GRADE A MOCK DRAFT, MEANING
THESE ARE THE PLAYERS HE THINKS
BEST FIT EACH TEAM'S NEEDS, NOT
THE ONES HE BELIEVES THEY WILL
NECESSARILY SELECT.
MCSHAY THINKS THE CARDINALS,
GIANTS, AND BRONCOS SHOULD GO
WITH QUARTERBACKS, AND THE
RAIDERS SHOULD FORTIFY THEIR
PASS RUSH WITH KENTUCKY'S JOSH
ALLEN.
WE ARE JOINED NOW BY THE MAN
HIMSELF.
YOU HAVE THREE QUARTERBACKS
GOING IN THE TOP 10.
WALK US THROUGH YOUR THOUGHT
PROCESS ON EACH, STARTING WITH
KYLER MURRAY AT NUMBER ONE.
TODD: IT'S A TOUGH CALL,
BECAUSE YOU'RE TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT WHAT THE ORGANIZATION
NEEDS.
AND HONESTLY, IF I'M THE
GENERAL MANAGER AND I'M LOOKING
AT THIS SITUATION, IF KLIFF
KINGSBURY COMES IN AND HE WANTS
THIS QUARTERBACK, I GOT TO GET
HIM THE QUARTERBACK.
AND THAT'S REALLY YOUR JOB AS
RUNNING THE
DEPARTMENT.
I THINK HE FITS THE SYSTEM
WELL.
JOSH ROSEN COULD WORK.
I THINK THERE'S SOME CONCERN
WITH LONG-TERM DURABILITY.
YOU HAVE THE POINT GUARD
MENTALITY, LIKE KYLER HAS.
AND LISTEN, THIS AIR RAID
DOESN'T ALWAYS HAVE TO HAPPEN.
HE BRINGS THAT, AND SO THAT'S
AN EXTRA ELEMENT.
DWAYNE HASKINS, ANOTHER TOUGH
ONE TO FIGURE OUT.
IT'S LIKE EVERY WEEK A
GUY FALLING, AND THERE'S A GUY
RISING.
HASKINS IS THE  POCKET
PASSER IN THIS DRAFT.
THERE ARE SOME CONCERNS ABOUT
OFIENCE.
SAME CAN BE SAID FOR KYLER
BOTH 14 STARTS, COMPARED TO
DREW LOCK, WHO'S GOT 46.
BUT THIS GUY, FROM INSIDE THE
POCKET, YOU GIVE HIM JUST A
LITTLE BIT OF TIME, HE CAN DICE
YOU UP.
AND THEN FINALLY, DREW LOCK TO
ME IS THE MOST INTRIGUING OF
■ THREE, JUST BECAUSE HE'S
GOT 46■
HE'S THE MOST EXPERIENCED.
HIS TAPE IS THE MOST UP AND
DOWN, THOUGH, THE LEAST
CONSISTENT IN TERMS OF DECISION
MAKING AND WITH HIS ACCURAC■■■■
BUT I THINK WHEN HIS FEET ARE
RIGHT, HE'S REALLY GOOD IN
TERMS OF HIS ACCURACY.
AND THEN THE CONFIDENCE THAT HE
BRINGS, THE ATHLETICISM HE HAS,
THE BIG ARM, TEAMS ARE
SBREEFPLGD IT'S GOING TO BE
INTERESTING.
JAY: HE'D BE THE THIRD MISSOURI
Q.B. TO GO IN THE FIRST ROUND
AND FIRST SINCE BLAINE GABBERT
IN 2011.
TODD: AND THAT WENT WELL.
JAY: YEAH, I WAS GOING SAY,
WE'RE NOT JUMPING UP AND DOWN
OVER THAT ONE.
THE PACKERS HAVE A PAIR OF
PICKS IN THE FIRST ROUND.
YOU HAVE THEM TAKING A COUPLE
OF PLAY MAKERS TO HELP OUT
AARON RODGERS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK THEY SNOW
MARQUISE BROWN AND IRV SMITH
JR.?
TODD: I THINK EVERYONE IS
SAYING D.J. METCALF BECAUSE
HE'S A BIGGER GUY.
HE'S 228 POUNDS, RAN A 4.33 40.
I UNDERSTAND HE'S A PHYSICAL
FREAK.
I JUST THINK THE BETTER
FOOTBALL PLAYER IS MARQUISE ■OW.
WHEN I STUDY THE TAPE, SPEED,
QUICKNESS,■ EXPLOSION, THE
ABILITY TO WATCH THAT ROUTE, I
HIS ABILITY TO SEPARATE
ALSO CREATE AFTER■■ THE CATCH
MAKES HIM I THINK UNIQUE.
A LOT OFo; DESEAN JACKSONISM TO
■■■O■Q& v ■■,é■
I KNOWY÷S HE HAS THE LISFRANC
INJURY.
BUT TO ME, MARQUISE BROWNING
WHEN SHE HE'S HEALTHY AND 100%,
HE'S THE BEST WIDE RECEIVER IN
THIS CLASS.
AND THEN IF YOU BRING IN A
RECEIVER EARLY, GO GET A TIGHT
■■■■■■■■■■■■ YOU CAN.
AND■NK GREEN BAY HAS■■■■/
GOTTEN TORTUNITY■=■■k■■RITH
çDS FIRST
ú# POTENTIALLY IN THIS
YEAR'S CLASS, IRV SMITH JR.
MAKES A LOT OF SENSE.
WHAT HE DOES BEST, JAY, IS
AFTER THE CATCH.
YOU DON'T SEE A LOT OF TIGHT
ENDS CREATE AS MANY Y
H AS HE DOES, AND GOAT
BETTER AND BETTER AS A BLOCKER.
SO IF IT'S NOT IRV SMITH JR.,
IT COULD BE HOP KIN SON, FROM
IOWA, BUT WITH THE 12TH PICK.
I THINK PLAYMAKERS ARE
CRITICAL, EVEN THOUGH THEY NEED
AN EDGE RUSHER.
BUT I THINK THEY'VE GOT TO GET
SOME MORE PLAYMAKERS AROUND
AARON RODGERS.
JAY: THIS NOTE I DIDN'T KNOW,
GREEN BAY HASN'T TAKEN AN
OFFENSIVE SKILL PLAYER IN THE
FIRST ROUND SINCE GENTLEMAN WON
WALKER IN 2002.
TODD: THEY DIDN'T REALLY
PARTICIPATE IN FREE AGENCY
UNTIL THIS YEAR, TOO.
HOPEFULLY FOR AARON RODGERS'
SAKE, THINGS ARE CHANGING.
JAY: TODD MCSHAY, THANKS.
CARR SNOW
CARI: NOW TO "SPORTSCENTER,"
BREAKING NEWS.
UCLA HAS HIRED CINCINNATI'S
MICK CRONIN HAS THE NEW HEAD
COACH.
HE'LL REPLACE STEVE ALFORD, WHO
WAS LET GO BY UCLA DURING THE
SEASON.
THE BRUINS' COACHING SEARCH
TINING WINDING PATH TO GET TO
CRONIN, WHO HAS BEEN AT
CINCINNATI SINCE 2006.
THIS YEAR THE BEARCATS FINISHED
SECOND IN THE A.A.C.
CINCINNATI EARNED A NUMBER
SEVEN SEED IN THIS YEAR'S NCAA
TOURNAMENT, BUT GOT KNOCKED OUT
IN THE FIRST ROUND.
HERE'S MORE ABOUT HIS RESUME OF
MICK CRONIN.
HE BRINGS THIS TO THE TAVENL
HE'S BEEN A HEAD COACH FOR 16
YEARS, INCLUDING THE LAST 13 AT
CINCINNATI.
PRETTY STABLE.
THIS YEERK THE BEARCATS
FINISHED WITH A 28-7 RECORD,
AND CRONIN MADE HIS 11TH
TOURNAMENT APPEARANCE.
CRONIN WILL TRY TO BRING UCLA
BACK TO ITS WINNING WAYS.
■>
JAY: COMING UP NEXT -- WHY
PRINCE -- YES, PRINCE -- COULD
BE READY FOR A GAME OF
BASKETBALL ANYS■q■S■S■ TIME, AN
ANY PLACE.
>> YOU ARE WEARING A BLOUSE.
>> I CALL A SHIRT WITH RUFFLES.
I switched to Liberty Mutual,
because they let me
customize my insurance.
And as a fitness junkie,
I customize everything,
like my bike, and my calves.
Liberty Mutual customizes
for what yay
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
Don't you get the
best price booking at
one of those travel sites?
They tell you that,
but when you book at Hilton.com,
you get the
Price Match Guarantee.
So if you find your room at
a lower rate, Hilton is like...
We're gonna match that rate
ve you an extra 25% off.
What would travel sites do
if you found a better price?
That's not my problem,
it's your problem.
a here!■
Whoa, I reallyhat perf.
It's just acting,
I'm really good at it.
Book at Hilton.com and get the
Hilton Price Match Guarantee.
I like to make my life easy.
If you find a lower rate,
we match it and give you=■■/
( ♪♪ )
Romo mode.
(Beep)
(Bang)
Good luck
with that one.
Yes!
That's why I wear
Skechers Slip-Ons.
They're effortless.
Just slip them
right on and off.
Skechers
Slip-Ons,
with
Air-Cooled
Memory Foam.
The final whistle
was just the start...
Of an epic weekend away.
Book your flights, hotels,
and car on Expedia
and travel like a champion.
Expedia.
Someone is going to be the
first.
Someone is going to make waves.
Someone is going to blow up the
game.
Someone is going to reinvent a
classic.
Someone is going to start from
scratch.
Someone is going to break
barriers.
Someone is going to do that
thing you really, really want to
do.
It might as well be you.
I can't tell you who I am
or what I witnessed,
but I can tell you Liberty
Mutual customized my
car insurance so I only
pay for what I need.
Oh no, no, no, no,
no, no, no...
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
TCHOIP YEAR'S NCAA MEN'S
BASKETBALL CHAMPIONSHIP WAS
DECIDED IN MINNEAPOLIS.
THAT CITY HAD ITS OWN HOOPS
HISTORY FROM.
BUDDING CAREER OF KEVIN MCHALE
TO AN INFAMOUS FIGHT BETWEEN
OHIO STATE AND THE UNIVERSITY
OF MINNESOTA BACK IN 1972.
BUT FROM ITS INDOOR ARENAS TO
THE PURR FEWING WATERS OF LAKE
MINNETONKA.
CHRIS CONNELLY SHARES THE STORY
OF AN UNKNOWN BASKETBALL STAR,
PRINCE.
YES, THAT ONE.
THE SYMBOL.
HE WAS, IN FACT, A 5'2" POINT
GUARD WHO NEEDED JUST ONE NAME
TO CONQUER THE WORLD.
>> THIS IS "SC FEATURED."
THIS IS THE POWER OF SPORTS.
>> DEARLY BELOVED.
WE ARE GATHERED HERE TODAY TO
THIS THIS THING CALLED LIFE.
ELECTRIC WORD LIFE THAT MEANS
FOREVER AND THAT'S A MIGHTY
LONG TIME.
BUT I'M HERE TO TELL YOU.
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE.
♪ IN THIS LIFE, YOU'RE ON YOUR
OWN ♪
EU DOWN ♪P■>■> YEARS AFTER HIS
DEATH, PRI■■■■w■■■■■w■■■w■■■w■■
HOMETOWN OF MINNEAPOLIS AS THE
MOST ELECTRIFYING SONGWRITER,
LIVE PERFORMER, AND VIRTUOSO OF
HIS ERA.
BUT AS HIS FELLOW MUSICIANS
LEARN AND FRIENDS COME NEW,
PRINCE ROGERS NELSON HAD
ANOTHER SET OF SPECTACULAR
SKILLS.
YEARS BEFORE HIS MUSIC SET THE
WORLD ON FIRE, PRINCE MADE A
NAME FOR HIMSELF ON THE COURT,
OUTSIDE PARK AVENUE UNITED MET
DISS CHURCH IN SOUTH
MINNEAPOLIS.■■■F2■F2■■■■■■■ FIR
SIXTH GRADE.
PRINCE WAS VERY ATHLETIC.
TO ME, HIS BIGGEST■F2F2F F■■■■■
AND## HIS QUICKNESS.
CHRIS: FROM THE#c#■## CHURCH LE
JUNIOR HIGH, FROM SEVENTH NT
THROUGH NINTH GRADE.P
PRINCE AT POINT GUARD.
>> YOU HAD TO BE READY FOR A
NO-LOOK PASS FROM PRINCE BACK
IN THE DAY.
HE JUST HAD THAT ABILITY TO
DECIPHER, CREATE, AND THEN
IMPLEMENT A PLAY JUST ON THE
SPOT.
HE WOULD TAKE OFF RUNNING AND
ZIGZAG AND DO ALL THOSE TYPES
OF THINGS, AND HIS SPEED, THEY
COULDN'T CATCH HIM.
>> THE AFRO WAS ABOUT TWO FEET
HIGH, SO HE WAS AT THAT TIME
STILL THE SMALLEST GUY ON THE
COURT.
PRINCE WASN'T A GREAT SHOOTER.
BUT HE WAS SO FAST AND SO QUICK
WITH PASSING.
CHRIS: CENTRAL HIGH BASKETBALL
COACH AL NUNES WAS SCOUTING
WHAT WAS THEN REGARDED AS A
ONCE-IN-A-GENERATION GROUP OF
MANY OF AYERS WOL■L■■■■ST■■■■■■
TEAM AT CENTRAL, BUT PRINCE
WOULD NOT BE AMONG THEM.
>> WE WERE PLAYING, AND ALL OF
A SUDDEN PRINCE WALKS OFF.
HE LEAVES.
HE'S GOT TO CATCH THE BUS.
YOU KNOW, SMED MUSIC
COMMITMENTS.
>> YOU COULD SEE PRINCE START
TO WEAN AWAY FROM THE GAME.
CHRIS: EVEN WITH THE FAME AND
THE GLOBAL SUCCESS, THE GAME
STAYED WITH HIM.
EVEN PRINCE'S PERSONAL
PHOTOGRAPHER WOULD SEE HIM
SHOOTING HOOPS AT PRINCE'S
COMPOUND, PAISLEY PARK IN
CHANHASSEN, MINNESOTA.
>> IN THE LOADING DOCK, THERE
WERE TWO BASKETBALL HOOPS AT
THE OPPOSITE END THAT HAVE
LOADING AREA.
WE SHOT SOME PHOTOS OF HIM
OUTSIDE, WHERE HE WAS JUST
MESSING WITH THE BASKETBALL,
JUST SPINNING ON HIS FINGER AND
ALL THAT.
IF YOU'VE EVER WATCHED A LIVE
SHOW OF HIS, HE MOVED LIKE AN
ATHLETE ALL THE TIME.
HE'D JUMP ON TOP OF HIS PIANO
IN FIVE-INCH HEELS.
I THINK A LOT OF ATHLETES
COULDN'T DO THAT.
>> WE ALWAYS WORE HIGH HEELS
WHEN WE PLAYED, SO WE'RE REALLY
GOOD AT PLAYING TPWHAB OUR
HEELS, WHICH IS CRAZY, BUT WE
DID.
CHRIS: YOU PLAYED BASKETBALL IN
YOUR HEELS?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
CHRIS: DURING HER MID 1980'S
COLLABORATIONS WITH PRINCE,
PERCUSSIONIST AND SINGER SHEILA
E. SAYS THE TWO WOULD BREAK
FROM RECORDING TO HIT THE
COURT.
>> HE WAS A GREAT BASKETBALL
PLAYER.
HE REALLY WAS.
HE COULD PLAY, NO JOKE.
CHRIS: NOW, WHEN YOU'D BE
PLAYING HORSE OR PIG, WHAT KIND
OF A SHOOTER WAS HE?
>> DID HE PRETTY GOOD, BUT DID
I BETTER.
I WAS BETTER THAN HIM IN
THREE-POINT SHOTS.
THIS IS ONE THING HE REALLY
DID.
IF I DID SOMETHING THAT WAS
SILLY LIKE I WOULD GET THE
BASKETBALL AND THEN I WOULD
BOUNCE, I'D SAY YOU HAVE TO DO
THIS, I BOUNCE, I DID SOMETHING
LIKE THIS, AND THEN YOU TURN
AND GO LIKE THIS.
AND IF I MADE, IT HE'D LIKE,
I'M NOT DOING IT.
THEN TAKE A LETTER.
HE WOULD GET MAD AT ME DOING
SILLY THINGS LIKE THAT.
IT'S JUST PART OF WHAT WE DID
EVERY DAY OR, YOU KNOW, WHEN
WE'RE RECORDING OR EVEN AT
PAISLEY.
YOU KNOW, WE'D JUST PLAY.
CHRIS: NEWS OF PRINCE'S FINEST
HOUR ON A BASKETBALL COURT
EMERGED ON FEBRUARY 18, 2004,
WHEN TV'S CHAPELLE SHOW AIRED
ONE OF CHARLIE MURPHY'S TRUE
HOLLYWOOD STORY.
>> WE IN THE CLUB, AND PRINCE
CAME IN.
THAT'S WHEN "PURPLE RAIN" CAME
OUT AND PRINCE WAS THE [BEEP],
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
CHRIS: THE SKETCH TELLS THE
STORY OF AN AFTER-HOURS PICKUP
GAME BACK IN 1985 THAT PITTED
COMEDIAN EDDIE MURPHY'S CREW
VERSUS PRINCE AND HIS PALS.
THE DAZZLING IMPRESSION OF
PRINCE WAS PURE COMEDIC GOLD.
>> HE'S WITH HIS WHOLE CREW,
AND HE HAD HIS OTHER CAT NAMED
MICKEY FREE.
AND MICKEY FREE WAS LIKE THE
NEW CAT, WHEN HE JOIN THE
GROUP, I HEARD MAD CATS GO
SHALOMAR GOT A NEW GIRL.
>> IT WAS RIGHT ON.
I LAUGH EVEN NOW ABOUT IT.
CHRIS: MICKEY FREE, THEN WITH
THE GROUP SHALOMAR, SUGGEST A
DETAIL THAT DIDN'T MAKE IT INTO
THE CHAPELLE SKETCH, FUELING
PRINCE'S FIRE TO GET ON THE
COURT.
>> EDDIE MURPHY BROUGHT BIG
BOOM BOX WITH HIS NEW SONG
"PARTY ALL THE TIME."
PRINCE IS LIKE, LET'S PLAY
BASKETBALL.
>> THIS BORES ME.
IS ANYONE UP FOR A GAME OF
BASKETBALL?
>> JUST LIKE THAT.
AND I WAS LIKE, WHAT DID PRINCE
JUST SAY?
BECAUSE THEY'RE IN CLUB
CLOTHES, FROM THE CLUB, RIGHT?
YOU WERE WEARING A BLOUSE.
WELL, I CALL A SHIRT WITH
RUFFLES, CHRIS, YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M SAYING?
>> WHAT YOU KNOW WE GOING TO
CALL THIS?
THE SHIRT AGAINST THE BLOUSE.
>> PRINCE BRINGS IT IN, AND I'M
EVEN KIDDING WHEN I TELL YOU
THIS, HE WAS LIKE STEPH CURRY,
BABY.
THEN HE GOES TO THE FAR RIGHT
CORNER, FADEAWAY JUMP SHOT,
NOTHING BUT NET.
>> GOOD.
IN YOUR FACE, CHARLIE MURPHY.
>> PRINCE MASSACRED THOSE GUYS.
IT WAS UNREAL.
>> GAME.
BLOUSES.
>> ALL RIGHT, HE BEAT YOU IN
BASKETBALL, AND THEN WHAT
HAPPENED?
>> AFTER IT WAS ALL OVER, HE
TOOK US IN THE HOUSE AND SERVED
US PANCAKES.
>> IT WAS ONE OF MY SHOWS
AFTER, AND HE'S GOING, DID YOU
SEE THE SKIT?
YEAH, YEAH, SIT DOWN.
AND THEN WE'RE JUST SITTING,
CHILLING, AND OUT OF NO I JUST
SAID, DAVE, SOME SOME PANCAKES?
CHRIS: TODAY, FOR THOSE WHO
RECALL HIM ON THE COURT, WHERE
HIS ZPHRARE CHARISMA STOOD OUT
JUST LIKE THEY DID ON STAGE,
LOOKING BACK STILL BRINGS A
SMILE.
>> ♪ YOU KNOW THE ONE
DR. EVERYTHING WILL BE ALL
RIGHT ♪
>> EVEN TODAY, YOU KNOW, IT'S
PRETTY SURREAL FOR ME TO LISTEN
TO SOME OF HIS MUSIC AND THINK
THAT'S THE SAME GUY WE USED TO
HANG OUT WITH, YOU KNOW, BEHIND
THE CHURCH ON PARK AVENUE,
PLAYING MIDDLE SCHOOL
BASKETBALL.
ACTUAL PICTURE THE AFRO, THAT'S
THE SAME GUY.
PRETTY AMAZING.
JAY: WELL DONE, CHRIS CONNELLY.
çg■u THAT DUDE.
I REALLY DO.
COMING UP ON "SP■
FIRST TODD MS AARON
RODGERS GETTING HELP, NOW
SCOMMAUTH TIM HASSELBECK JOIN
US IN STUDIO WITH
REACTION TO THE PACKERS Q.B.
FIRING BACK AT POINTED
CRITICISM.
THAT'S ON THE WAY, 1:00 P.M.
EASTERN, WE SHIFT OVER TO ESPN2
FOR NEWSRENCE AT■AUGUT HE HAS T
HE TAKES AIM AT HIS FIRST
MASTERS TITLE SINCE 2005.
♪ ♪■♪
♪ Goin' down the only road
I've ever known ♪
♪ Like a drifter I was-- ♪
♪ Born to walk alone! ♪
Keep goin' man!
You got it!T
If you rúou get it.úúú
♪ Here I go again ♪
GEICO Motorcyc■
15 minutes could save you
15% or more.
Huge mistake.
Kevin Harvick?
Choose Mobil 1
Synthetic instead.
It protects engines better
than conventional motor oil.
Yea you would say that,
you're whe logo.
How about now?
Get 250,000 miles
of protection.
Upgrade to Mobil 1.
■hyD;yD;hhD;D;■y■D;■■y■■h■■■■■■&
MY T■■■■■Ñ■■   >>>>> L
IT'S BEEN WORN DOWN
TO UGLY THIN GRASS!
■■■■  WITH A SOIL IMPROVER
TO STRENGTHEN ROOTS!
THE REVOLUTION■>ñ>
NOW SOLU WS.■7OTTS THICK'R LA
SEED TO FILL IN GAPS!
■/  AND FE TO FE
S TO TO FILL IN GAPS!
A 50% THICKER
■/AFTER ON.TO FE
♪ ♪ ♪
■N■■■
W YARD TIME IS OUR TIME.
THIS IS A SC■
♪
(Brad)
Wow. Fusion. The process of
two things becoming one.
It's like, when the right renter
and the perfect home
are joined...
...becoming the best version
of themselves.
On Apartments-dot-com,
not only can you find a new
place but you can find...
new meaning.
(Little Boy)
Look, Mom! Toby's a couch!
(Brad)
And Toby's a couch.
(Little Boy)
Who's a good couch?
(Brad)
Apartments-dot-com.
Change your apartment.
Change the world.
CARI: BREAKING NEWS TO
"SPORTSCENTER."
PIRATES STARTING PITCHER CHRIS
ARCHER HAS BEEN SUSPENDED FIVE
GAMES AND REDS OUTFIELDER
YASIEL PUIG FOR THEIR TWO ROLES
IN A BENCH-CLEARING BRAP
SUNDAY.
ARCHERHREWGuREDS BATTER
DEREK DEITRICH, BENCHES
CLEARED, AND JUST AS THINGS
SEEMED TO CALM DOWN, YOU CAN
SEE YASIEL PUIG CHARGING.
PIRATES PLAYERS TRYING TO TAKE
ON THE WHOLE TEAM.
REDS MANAGER DAVID BELL ALSO
HAS BEEN SUSPENDED A GAME.
ALL THREE HAVE BEEN FINED AN
UNDISCLOSED AMOUNT.
TO THAT VEIN, WE WANT TO LET
YOU KNOW, WE GOT YOUR BASEBALL.
RED SOX'S HOME OPENER AT FENWAY
PARK, CHRIS SALE GETS THE START
FOR THE DEFENDING CHAMPS WHEN
THEY TAKE ON THE BLUE JAYS AT
2:00 P.M. EASTERN.
THEN AT 8:00 CENTRAL, WE'LL
HAVE THE SECOND GAME OF A
THREE-GAME SERIES BETWEEN THE
YANKEES AND STROS.■]■]
JAY: TIME FOR THE BLEACHER
REPORT STORY WAS PUBLISHED
■÷ DETAILING A FRACTURED
RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN RODGERS
AND MIKE MCCARTHY.
TENSIONS REPORTEDLY GO ALL THE
ON RODGERS WITH THE FRTHY WAS A
OF THE 8 2005 DRAFT.
FORMER PACKERS WERE QUOTED,
JERMICHAEL FINLEY SAID HE WAS A
BAD LEADER, AND GREG JENNINGS
CALLED HIM ULTRASENSITIVE.
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT A
MYSTERY.
THIS WAS A SMEAR ATTACK BY, YOU
KNOW, A WRITER LOOKING TO
ADVANCE HIS CAREER, TALKING
PLAYERS WHO ALL HAVE AN AGEND  ■
WHETHER THEY'RE ADVANCING THEIR
OWN CAREERS OR JUST TRYING TO
STIR OLD STUFF UP.
■8■8■8■8■s■C OF THE ARTICLE SEE
WANT TO SAY, YOU KNOW, THE
PACKERS ARE WORRIED ABOUT ME AS
THE LEADER OF THE FOOTBALL TEAM
MOVING FORWARD F. THEY KNEW
THAT, WHY WOULD THEY OFFER ME A
CONTRACT LAST YEAR?
AND TWO, IF I REALLY DISL
MICH, WHY WOULD I RE-SIGN?
KNOWING IF IXp■■8 P, AND WE
DO WHAT WE DO AROUND HERE, IT'S
GOING TO BE ME AND MIKE MY
ENTIRE CAREER.
SO IF I REALLY DISLIKED HIM
THAT MUCH, YOU THINK I'D
RE-SIGN?
AM I REALLY THAT -- IS THE
MONEY THAT IMPORTANT TO ME?
I LOVE MCCARTHY.
MIKE HAS BEEN A HUGE PART OF MY
SUCCESS AND MY CAREER.
AND I'VE HAD SOME AMAZING
MOMENTS ON AND OFF THE FIELD
WITH MIKE.
JAY: TIM AND MATT HASSELBECK
JACOBY: US NOW ON
"SPORTSCENTER."
TIM, LET'S START WITH YOU.
AARON CALLED IT A SMEAR
CAMPAIGN.
WHAT WAS YOUR REACTION?
TIM: I THINK WHAT'S INTERESTING
ABOUT THIS FOR ME WITH AARON
RODGERS  DOES AARON LOOK
GOOD IN THE BLEACHER REPORT
ARTICLE?
NO, HE DOES NOT.
BUT REALLY, IT WAS MIKE
MCCARTHY THAT LOOKED THE WORST.
WHAT AARON WAS DOING, YEAH, HE
STUCK UP FOR HIMSELF A LITTLE
BIT, BUT HE REALLY WAS TRYING
TO CLEAR THE AIR FOR MIKE
MCCARTHY.
WHAT AARON REALLY DID WAS
BASICALLY S■  MIKE
MCCARTHY, HE'S BEEN A HUGE PART
OF MY SUCCESS IN MY CAREER.
HIVE GREAT MOMENTS WITH HIM ON
AND OFF THE FIELD.
THERE'S NO WAY THAT I -- LIKE,
I WANTED TO PLAY FOR HIM, WE
WHAT HE WAS SAYING ON THE ND
RADIO, HEaaa■a■a■a■a■■■■■■■■■■■
SAY THANK YOU TO HIM FOR THE
GOOD JOB HE D. I ACTUALLY
THOUGHT THAT WAS FAIRLY
SELFLESS OF AARON RODGERS TO
STICK UP FOR A GUY THAT HE NO
LONGER PLAYS FOR.
MATT: I WOULD COMPLETELY AGREE
WITH ALL OF THAT.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S JUST KIND OF
THE STAR LEVEL THAT AARON
RODGERS IS AT RIGHT NOW.
I MEAN, SOMETIMES YOU'RE A
STAR, YOU DO ONE LITTLE THING,
IT'S NEWSWORTHY.
HE DIDN'T EVEN DO ANYTHING.
LIKE THIS ARTICLE CAME OUT OF
NOWHERE.
IT REMINDS ME A LITTLE BIT OF
THE FEW LAST YEAR THAT WAS BILL
BELICHICK THAT CAN'T GET ALONG.
THE YEAR BEFORE THAT AROUND
THIS OFF-SEASON, IT WAS, YOU
KNOW, RUSSELL WILSON, PETE
CARROLL, AND THE LEGION OF
BOOM.
THIS YEAR, IT'S THE GREEN BAY
PACKERS' TURN.
AND HOW THEY MOVE FORWARD FROM
THIS WILL BE TELLING, BUT I
ALSO THINK COME AUGUST THIS
WILL N SOMETHING THAT
WE'R.= TALKING ABOUT.
ALL EYES WILL BE ON AARON
RODGERS, YES, BUT THEY'RE
ALREADY ON AARON RODGERS AS WE
SAW THIS WEEK.
JAY: HE MENTIONED "MOSTLY
IRRELEVANT, BITTER PLAYERS"
ATTACKING HIM, SEEMINGLY A
REFERENCE TO FIN SCOMPLEE
JENNINGS.
I'LL STICK WITH YOU, DO YOU FEE
NECESSARY THAT
CHARACTERIZATION?
MATT: TO ME, WHAT I FEEL LIKE
HE MEANT WAS IRRELEVANT TO THE
RELATIONSHIP.
YOU KNOW, SO I REMEMBER I
PLAYED 10 YEARS IN SEATTLE.
MIKE HOLMGREN WAS MY HEAD COACH
MOST OF THAT TIM■1■í■■■WE ■n OF
COULD PROBABLY GUESS WHAT OUR
WAS ACb=■■=■/WAS LIKE, BUT IT
PEOPLE THAT■= ACTUALLY KNEW WHA
THAT RELATIONSHIP WAS LIKE.
THIS SUMMER I HAD A CHANCE TO
SIT DOWN WITH MIKE MCCARTHY,
ONE OF MY OLD POSITION COACHES,
SAT DOWN WITH HIM, WHAT IS YOUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH AARON RODGERS
REALLY LIKE?
AND WHAT HE DESCRIBED WAS
ALMOST EXACTLY WHAT AARON
RODGERS DESCRIBED YESTERDAY.
THESE GUYS DID GET ALONG.
■c) CONFLICT, SOME
CREATIVE TENSION BETWEEN PLAY
CALLER ANDD COACH AND
QUARTERBACK?
ABSOLUTELY.
IS THAT NORMAL IN THE NFL?
HECK, YEAH.
THAT'S NORMAL.
AND SO I THINK PROBABLY WHAT HE
MEANT BY THAT WAS, PEOPLE THAT
WOULD BE NOT IN THE KNOW ABOUT
HOW IT REALLY IS BETWEEN TWO
GUYS THAT HAVE BEEN WORKING
TOGETHER A LONG TIME.
TIM: SAYING MOSTLY IRRELEVANT
PLAYERS COMES ACROSS AS BAD.
TARGETSE I ALSO THINK WHAT HE'S
SAYING IS GREG JENNINGS AND
JERMICHAEL FINLEY HAVEN'T BEEN
IN THAT LOCKER ROOM FOR A LONG
TIME.
SOMEBODY THAT MAYBE, YOU KNOW,
MAY IN THE LOCKER ROOM FOR A
PART OF A TEAM FOR A SHORT
PERIOD OF TIME OVER A STRETCH
OF OVER A DECADE, MAYBE SAW
SOME CONFLICTS, BUT THAT
DOESN'T MEAN THAT'S WHAT THE
ENTIRE RELATIONSHIP IS ABOUT.
AND SO THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING.
I THINK THAT'S WHY HE PROBABLY
CAME OUT AS STRONGLY AS HE DID
IN TERMS OF THOSE ATTACKS, YOU
KNOW --
JAY: AND TULSA FELT LIKE AN
ATTACK ON THE WRITER.
MATT: THE GUY WHO WROTE THE
PIECE.
YOU'RE GOING TO DO A BIG PIECE
ON ME AND MIKE MCCARTHY AND THE
PEOPLE YOU CHOSE TO TALK TO ARE
THESE GUYS?
WHY DENT YOU TALK SOME PEOPLE
THAT ARE HERE NOW, OR PEOPLE
THAT WOULD REALLY KNOW?
THERE'S SOME ANGER IN HIS
VOICE, NO DOUBT.
AND I THINK WE SAW A SIDE OF
AARON RODGERS THAT WE HAVEN'T
SEEN MUCH OF.
JAY: SEVERND FORMER
PACKERS CAME TO THE DEFENSE OF
RODGERS IN THE PAST FEW DAYS,
JAMES JONES, CASEY.
WE'LL SEE IF THIS IS THE END OF
THIS OR IF THERE WILL BE MORE.
MATT, TIM, THANK YOU, GUYS.
CARI: JAY, COMING UP AT THE TOP
OF THE HOUR, WE'RE HEADING TO
ESPN2.
WE WILL TAKE YOU LIVE TO■z■z■z
WOODS' MASTERS NEWS CONFERENCE.
UP NOKES ESPN, IT'S KARL RAVECH
AND "BASEBALL TONIGHT."
Hmm. Exactly.
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay
for what you need.
Nice. But, uh...
what's up with
your... partner?
Not again. LiMu
that's your reflection.
Only pay fed.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
You can't always believe
what you see. Like if ,
B■
hidden in the depths
of this soft taco,
you'd find Crunchy...
Melty...
Nachos.
For just one dollar.
Would you believe me?
Or are you just seeing things?
The new $1 Loaded Nacho Taco
from T's Cravings
Valu
Value Be■ò■=
With Graer,
that will lead you to somewhere
unexpected.tional
Somewhere you can create
something...
better than good.
Here, you'll create something
grand.
Grand Marnier.
A visionary blend of fine cognac
and bitter orange liqueur.
Live Grand.
The Lexus ES.
Every curve, eveti
A product of mastery.
Lease the 2019 ES 350 for
$389 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
I STOOD OUTSIDE, ASSESSING
THE SITUATION.
I KNEW IT COULD ROUGH IN THERE,
BUT HOW ROUGH?
THERE WAS NO WAY TO
KNOW FOR SURE.
HEY GUYS....
DADDY, IT'S PINK!
BUT HEY. A NEW HOUSE IT'S A
BLANK CANVAS.
AND WE GOT A GREAT ONE
THANKS TO A REALLY LOW
MORTGAGE RATE
FROM NAVY FEDERAL CREDIT UNION.
PINK
SO SHE'S A PRINCESS.
YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
OORAH
NAVY FEDERAL CREDIT UNION.
OUR MEMBERS,
ARE THE MISSION.
JAY: BASEBALL ON ESPN2, MOOKIE
BETTS AND HIS TEAMMATES LIKELY
THINKING NO PLACE LIKE HOME,
EVEN IF IT IS A LITTLE CHILLY.
RED SOX HOME OPENER AGAINST
TORONTO, "BASEBALL T
BEGINS OUR COVERAGE.
HERE'S KARL RAVECH.
JAY: LET'S DO SOME "TOP PLAYS."
I'LL START, NUMBER 10,
CUBS-PIRATES.
CORNCH I■>■>■>■>■>■>■> B JUST T
ANDú R.B.I. SINGE, AND THE CUBS
WIN 10-0.
AND CUBS NEED ALL THE LOVE THEY
CAN GET.
CARI: JAY, I LOVE YOU, BECAUSE
NORMALLY I TAKE THE EVENS.
BUT I'LL TAKE THE ODD.
SOCCER, THE PASS, AND IT
SCORES, GOAL EASY.
THEY WOULD LOSE 4-1, THOUGH.
JAY: YOU WANT TO DO THE EIGHT?
CARI: NO, YOU'RE A GUEST.
THAT'S9■OU.
JAY: TO LEFT FIELD.
CHARLIE BUTLER.
CARI: YOU KNOW éyBUTLER?9
JAY: NO, I DON'T.
CARI: YOU KNOW CHARLIE MURPHY.
JAY: YES, I DO.
LOUISVILLE WINS THIS WIN.
CARI: BRAVES VISITING THE
ROCKIES.
BOTTOM NINE, ONE OUT.
HERE WE GO.
WOLTERS, FOUL BALL.
THERE YOU GO.
SWANSON RUNS ALL THE WAY FROM
SHORT AND DIVES.
THAT'S YOGA.
THAT OUTREACH THERE WITH THAT
ARM, THAT'S THAT YOGA THAT
THEY'RE DOING IN THE
OFF-SEASON.
MAYBE EVEN BEFORE THE GAME, WHO
KNOWS.
JAY, BACK AT YOU.
JAY: I LIKE HOW YOU DROPPED IT.
CONNECTICUT HIGH SCHOOL --
WELL, NO.
BASEBALL.
FAIRFIELD PREP'S JAY, DIVING
PLAY.
GETTING HIM READY IN HIGH
SCHOOL IN CONNECTICUT.
FAIRFIELD PREP LOSES 8-6.
CARI: HERE WE GO, GUYS.
COMING IN AT NUMBER FOUR,
TURKISH SUPER LEAGUE SOUTH
KOREA, THIS IS JAY'S FAVORITE.
THAT'S WHY HE DIDN'T WANT TO DO
IT.
THIS SHOT FOR THE GOAL.
OH, I'M IN THE WRONG WAY, JAY.
I WENT STRAIGHT TO FOUR.
I'M SORRY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS FIVE.
I TOOK YOURS.
ALD IT. CE YOU JUST DO IT, YOU
CARI: I JUST DID IT.
IT'S MY TURN.
[LAUGHTER]
SOCCER, JUMP AGO HEAD HERE.
YOU KNOW WHO WON, JAY.
JAY: OK, DIAL THREE.
I'LL DO THREE.
CARI: YOU DO THREE.
JAY: ASTROS AND YANKEES.
HARD-LINE DRIVE, ALEX BREGMAN,
DIDN'T HIT IT HARD ENOUGH.
CARI: NOT HARD ENOUGH, JAY.
AM I DOING THIS, NUMBER TWO?
JAY: YES, IT'S YOURS.
CARI: CHRISTIAN YELICH, DEEP
FLY BALL TO CENTER.
BUT G■■ÑÑOUT ROBBED HIM.
AND THAT'S BECAUSE HE MAKES
$400 MILLION, THAT'S WHY.
JAY: THERE YOU GO.
CARI: $400 MILLION, GOODNESS.
MEANWHILE, ANGELS WIN 5-2.
ALL YOU, MAN, NUMBER ONE.
JAY: OUR TOP PLAY, CHELSEA
TAKING ON WEST HAM UNITED.
OK, AID AN, WATCH THIS.
THAT MAN CAN PLAY.
CARI: CAN HE PLAY SOCCER?
JAY: OR FOOTBALL.
FINISHES WITH TWO GOALS IN
CHELSEA'S 2-0 WIN.
HE'S FAST.
HE'S SKILLED.
AND HE'S NUMBER ONE.
CARI: OH, SO LET'S TALK ABOUT
BOXING, SHALL WE?
DO YOU HAVE THE ESPN+ APP?
DO YOU?
THAT'S FINE.
11:00 EASTERN, AS IN DO YOU OWN
IT YOURSELF?
11:00 EASTERN, 10:00 EASTERN.
THESE TWO FIGHTS ARE EXCLUSIVE
ON ESPN+.
THEY'RE IN ENGLISH AND SPANISH.
START YOUR FREE TRIAL TODAY BY
DOWNLOADING THE ESPN APP OR
VISITING ESPNPLUS DOVEMENT I
WAS ASKING IF YOU HAD IT, IN
TERMS OF, YOU KNOW, AVAILABLE
AT YOUR FINGERTIPS.
JAY: OH, I COULD NOT HEAR YOU.
ACTUALLY I DO ON MY IPAD AND
PHONE.
CARI: TO■)■) STRASBURG
■ L NOLA AND
THE PH.OO
BOTH PITCHERS ARE 1-0 TO START
THE YEAR.
STRASBURG HAS A BETTER E.R.A.
JACOB DEGROM AND THE METS ARE
NALLS ACTION AS THEY H■nfn@na4■.
DEGROM IS HAVING A STELLAR
START TO THE YEAR.
■■ ■■■ú PITCHED.
THE RED SOX TRY TO RIGHT THE
SHIP.
CAN THEY DO IT CAN W CHRIS SALE
ON THE MOUND IN THEIR HOME
OPENER AGAINST THE BLUE JAYS?
YOU CAN CATCH THAT GAME, 2:00
P.M. EASTERN ON ESPN.
AND THAT NIFTY APP, AGAIN, THAT
I ASKED JAY IF HE HAD --
JAY: I LOVE THAT NIFTY APP.
"SPORTSCENTER," 6:00 P.M.
EASTERN AFTER "P.T.I.."
KEVIN NEGANDHI, KEITH OLBERMANN
LOOK AGENT HOW SOON THE LAKERS
MAKE MAJOR CHANGES.
PLUS THE AFTER-EFFECTS OF
TIGER'S COMMENTS TODAY AT THE
MASTERS.
AND REACTION TO JAMEIS
WINSTON'S PLAN TO PLAY 20
POUNDS HEAVIER THIS SEASON.
"SPORTSCENTER" AFTER "P.T.I."
ON ESPN  AND THE APP.
CARI: 20 POUNDS HEAVIER, WHAT
DOES THAT MEAN, JAY?
YOIP I DON'T KNOW.
SEEMS LIKE HE WOULD WANT TO GET
LIGHTER, BUT YOU KNOW, HE WANTS
TO DO WHAT HE WANTS TO DO.
CARI: HE HAS A PLAN.
IT'S BEEN GOOD.
WE'RE GOING TO DO THIS ON THE
OTHER NETWORK OF OURS CALLED
THE DEUCE.
JAY: "BASEBALL TONIGHT" NEXT ON
ESPN.
>> WELCOME, EVERYONE.
"BASEBALL TONIGHT" WE ARE■
1912 WAS THE FIRST HOME OPENER
AND HERE WE ARE IN 2019.
THERE'S BEEN SOME CHANGES.
TBEEN SOME MORE SERIES■■  THE