MICHAEL: KICK IT TO IT.
PAPI: THAT'S ALL THE TIME WE
HAVE FOR TODAY.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
DAN: OUR THANKS TO M<÷■÷
FOR SP?÷<÷?÷<÷<÷EEK WITH US.
NOW GET OUT OF HERE.
PAPI: YOU WON'T BE HERE NEXT
WEEK?
MICHAEL: NO, PAPI, I WON'T.
PAPI: OH!
OH!
YEAH!
[LAUGHTER]
[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
ESPN., INC.]
CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VISIT NCICAP.ORG
>> WHAT A FLY.
IT ALL STARTS TONIGHT, FINAL
FOUR.
ALSO, EASTERN CONFERENCE END
GAME AND A BUG ON A WINDSHIELD.
THE BUG ON THE WINDSHIELD WHICH
MAKES ME THINK OF THE TITLE ON
THEHIELD.
WHO'S GOT IT?
STICK TO IT.
>> I'M THE WINDSHIELD, NOT THE
BUG.
>> I GET THAT.
TONY:GHT THROUGH THIS.
MILWAUKEE LOCKING DOWN BEST
RECORD IN HOME THROUGHOUT.
EVERYTHING HAPPENED LAST NIGHT.
BLEDSOE AND EMBIID.
AND GIANNIS.■■CZ#■■
AND YOU PEOPLE LOVE THE GAMES.
IF PHILLY HAD WON -- BILL, WHAT
WAS THE STATEMENT THAT WAS MADE?
>> THE BUCKS ARE GOING TO BE
TOUGH THIS POST-SEASON.
I LOVE THE POST-SEASON AND
GIANNIS' FOUR BLOCKS OF EMBIID.
DESPITE OF THEIR INJURIES, THEY
ARE NOT GOING INTO THIS LIKE
THEY ARE SCARED.
THEY ARE ACTING LIKE THEY
BELONG.
TONY: WOODY PAIGE, HOW ABOUT
YOU?
>> THEY ARE GOING TO BE VERY
TOUGH IN THE POST-SEASON.
TONY: THEY SHOULD.
THEY HAVE THE BEST RECORD.
GIVE ME SOMETHING MORE, COME ON,
WOODY.
>> WHAT KIND OF STATEMENT DID
THEY MAKE?
IF THEY PLAY PHILADELPHIA AGAIN,
THE 76ERS ARE NOT GOING TO STEP
BACK OR DOWN, BUT ARE GOING TO
BE A TOUGH TEAM IN THAT SERIES
AND WITH THE HOME-COURT
ADVANTAGE THROUGHOUT THE
PLAYOFFS, IF THEY GET TO THE
TIMES, IT WILL CREATE PROBLEMS
FOR THE WARRIORS.
THEY HAVE SURVIVED THE INJURIES.
THEY STILL HAVE A FEW.
GIANNIS, M.V.P. OF THE LEAGUE AS
FAR AS I'M CONCERNED, THIS IS A
TEAM THAT IS GOING TO BE TOUGH
TO CONFRONT.
TONY: YOU SAY GIANNIS LOCKED
DOWN THE M.V.P.
THE FACT THAT WE ARE SAYING
THESE NUMBERS.
40-SOMETHING.
FIVE, SIX.
SARAH, WHAT WAS THE STATEMENT
FROM LAST NIGHT?
>> THING TO BE FAIR, OTHERWISE,
WE SAY IT'S A REGULAR SEASON
GAME AND DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
THE STATEMENT MADE BY THE BUCKS
IS ONE THEY HAVE BEEN MAKING ALL
SEASON BUT NOT EVERYONE HAS
BOUGHT.
IF THE CELTICS' TALENT COULD BE
MADE UP BY GETTING TOGETHER,
THEY WOULD BE THE FAVORITE.
SOME BELIEVE THE RAPTORS ARE THE
FAVORITE.
THE BUCKS HAVE BEEN THE BEST
TEAM.
THE INJURIES ARE THE ONLY THING
THAT COULD SLOW THEM DOWN.
HOME COURT ADVANTAGE.
THEY GET TO PLAY AT HOME IN
THOSE EARLY ROUNDS.
>> THE STATEMENT IS, WHERE HAVE
YOU BEEN.
AND I LIKE THE FACT THAT BLEDSOE
INITIATED THIS.
HE PUSHED HIM OFF AND THREW THE
BALL BACK AT HIM.
AND THE REASON WHY THE INJURY,
IS GEORGE HILL HAS COME BACK OUT
OF NOWHERE AND SCORED 60 POINTS
IN THE LAST TWO GAMES.
WHO KNEW THEY WERE GOING TO BE
[HORN]S POINT.■■■■■
TONY: GIANNIS CLINCH IT M.V.M.?
>> HIS BLOCK WITH EMBIID DID IT.
AND HE DOES EVERYTHING.
TONY: THE BLOCK ON EMBIID.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I THINK THE ONLY THING THAT WAS
KEEPING HARDEN WAS THE ABILITY
TO DO THE THINGS HE HAS HAD TO
DO TO GO FROM 11TH IN THE WEST.
30-PLUS-POINT GAMES.
THERE IS AN ASTER RISK ON THAT,
AS TO WHO COULD HAVE DONE THAT
AS WELL.
GIANNIS IS THE BEST PLAYER WITH
THE BEST RECORD.
ANYONE WHOSE TURN IT IS, --
TONY: WHOA.
WHOA.
NO.
LAST WORD FOR YOU.
>> GOT ALL THE NUMBERS.
EVERYTHING HAPPENED THERE.
THAT BEING ON THE ROAD WAS AIG■
FINAL FOURS TURN
AUBURN-GEORGIA TEXAS TECH
AND VA STATE.  SOUNDS LIKE A MO
'T ACQUIREx NREITZ.
NUMBER ONE DEFENSE VERSUS HAVING
A COACH WHO HAS BEEN THERE
BEFORE, WHAT IS MORE IMPORTANT,
SARAH?
>> WE HAVE UNDERESTIMATED TECH
SINCE THE BEGINNING.
THEY WERE PREDICTED TO FINISH
AND DIDN'T GET A VOTE.
THEY HAVE DONE TWO OTHER TEAMS
WHAT WE DIDN'T EXPECT OVER AND
OVER.
JUST BECAUSE MICHIGAN STATE
HASN'T LOST SINCE EARLY MARCH,
WE SHOULDN'T ASSUME THAT TEXAS
TECH TAKES THEM DOWN.
THE PRESSURE OF THE FINAL FOUR
AND HAVING A COACH LIKE IZZO.
I THINK THE WELL-ROUNDED TEAM
COMES OUT ON TOP.
TONY: NUMBER ONE DEFENSE IN THE
COUNTRY VERSUS A COACH WHO HAS
CHAMPIONSHIPS AND LIVES IN THE
FINAL FOUR, WHAT IS MORE
IMPORTANT?
>> TO ME, IT'S IZZO BUT FOR THE
REASONS OF ADJUSTMENT.
I ASKED THEM ABOUT THE GAME IN
D.C. AND I SAID YOU WON THIS
GAME WINNING SIX THREE THROWS.
IZZO IS THE GUY THAT WILL DO IT.
I LIKE IZZO.
BUT IN THIS GAME WITH THIS TEAM
AND THE SENIOR WHO TURNS IT ON.
TONY: ICE COLD FROM CLINTON
YATES.
NUMBER ONE DEFENSE, TEXAS TECH,
THEIR EFFICIENCY IS BETTER THAN
VIRGINIA.
THEY CAN PLAY THAT SLOG
BASKETBALL VERSUS MICHIGAN STATE
AND HOW ROUNDED THEY ARE.
>> THIS IS STILL ABOUT THE
PLAYERS.
TEXAS TECH IS GOING TO WIN THIS
GAME.
THEY HELD THE FOUR NCAA
OPPONENTS.
AND THEY CUT OFF WINSTON AND CUT
OFF THE HEAD OF THE SNAKE.
THAT'S HOW THEY BEAT MICHIGAN
STATE.
MOONY IS A GREAT DEFENDER.
AND TEXAS TECH.
TONY: YOU HAVE TEXAS TECH.
DEFENSE TRAVELS, THAT'S THE
EXPRESSION.
AND YOU THINK THAT'S GOING TO BE
KEY HERE, WOODY, HOW ABOUT YOU?
>> OFFENSE TRAVELS, THE
DEFENSIVE TEAM GETS THE BALL.
I'M GOING TO TAKE TOM IZZO, 1B
WOULD BE HAMILTON.
HAMILTON HAS MUCH EFFECT ON THE
FLOOR AS IZZO DOES ON OFF THE
FLOOR.
HE KNOWS WHAT IS GOING ON.
HE PROVIDED 50% OF THE ASSISTS
ON THEIR BASKETS.
AND I LIKE WHAT HE DOES
DEFENSIVELY AND OFFENSIVELY.1
[HORN]
TONY: WINSTON.
IT'S OK.
THAT WAS Ay TURNOVER.
WE STILL GOT MORE SHOW TO GO.
AUBURN AND VIRGINIA.
AND SLOG VERSUSG, WOODY,
PICK UP THE PIECES.
FOR AUBURN TO WIN, WH■■ TO
HAPPEN?
FOR VIRGINIA TO, WHAT NEEDS  HA?
>> IN THE CASE OF AUBURN, THEY
HAVE TO SET THE PACE.
WE KNOW ABOUT VIRGINIA WANTS TO
SLOW IT DOWN.
IF AUBURN GETS AHEAD, VIRGINIA
CAN'T COME BACK.
EVEN THOUGH THEY HAVE NEVER BEEN
A CHAMPION AND TO THE FINAL
FOUR, I LOVE THE COACH.
HE HAD SOME PROBLEMS WHEN HE
LEFT TENNESSEE, BUT HE HAS COME
BACK AND PROVED HE CAN COACH
GUYS DOWN THERE.
AND MISSING THEIR BEST PLAYER.
HARPER CAME THROUGH LAST WEEK.
PUT HIM ON THE FREE-THROW LINE,
IF YOU ARE VIRGINIA, YOU ARE NOT
GOING TO WIN THE GAME.
VIRGINIA'S DEFENSE IS NOT GOING
TO ABLE TO SLOW DOWN AUBURN.
AND SHE SHOOT THREE-POINTERS
BETTER THAN ANY TEAM AND THEY
ALL SHOOT THEM.
EVEN THE GUYS WHO CAN'T SHOOT
THEM.
TONY: YOU ARE GOING WITH THE
OFFENSE OVER THE DEFENSE.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
>> I'M GOING WITH U.V.A.
THERE IS CONCERN ABOUT THE PACE
AND WHETHER THEY CAN STAY IN THE
TOURNAMENT AND MANAGED TO GET
PAST IT.
MAYBE THE FIRST TIME WHEN
BENNETT IS RUNNING THIS STYLE
THEY HAVE A CORE OF THREE
PLAYERS TO TURN IT ON.
THEY DON'T HAVE TO REST ON THEIR
FUNDAMENTALS AND SLOW IT DOWN.
THEY CAN TAKE JEROME, GUY AND
HUNTER, THEY ARE SHOOTING 40%
FROM THREE AND COMBINE IT WITH
THEIR SOLID DEFENSE.
AND BOTH SIDES KIND OF GUY AND
AUBURN DEPENDS ON THE OFFENSE
AND HITTING THREES.
IF THEIR THREE-POINT SHOOTING
GOES DOWN, VIRGINIA CAN TAKE THE
LEAD AND NOT GIVE IT BACK.
>> THE OTHER THING THAT HUNTER
HAS BEEN REASONABLE,, AUBURN CAN
KEEP THAT GUY IN THE FRONTCOURT,
THEY HAVE A CHANCE.
FOR VIRGINIA TO WIN, CLARK HAS
BEEN A DEFENSIVE FORCE FOR THEM.
IF HE CAN FIND A WAY TO GET INTO
THIS GAME AND GET CLUTCH SHOTS.
HE IS A BIT OF A CONSTANT.
TONY: HAD ONE OF THE GREAT
PASSES.
HE IS PLAYING IN THIS
TOURNAMENT.
WE HAVE A COUPLE FOR VIRGINIA,
ONE FOR AUBURN.
YOU TALKED ABOUT HOW GREAT
DEFENSE IS FOR TEXAS TECH.
VIRGINIA IS RIGHT THERE.
>> AUBURN HAS A GREAT DEFENSE
AND AUBURN HAS SHOOTERS.
THE SECOND-MOST THREE-POINT
SHOOTERS OUTSIDE OF VILLANOVA.
AUBURN IS LIKE THE VILLANOVA,
NONE NBA GUYS AND ALL SHOOT
THREES.
BACKUP CENTER SHOT A THREE.
THEY WILL ALL COME OUT FIRING.
VIRGINIA CANNOT CATCH UP, THEY
CANNOT COME BACK.
[HORN]
>> WHICH GUY ARE YOU GOING TO
GET IT?
YOU KNOW FOR VIRGINIA TO SURVIVE
THEY HAVE TO GET GUYS SHOOTING
THREE-POINTERS.
>> IT'S ABOUT THAT GAME?
>> GUY WAS SO OPEN ABOUT THE
ANXIETY HE EXPERIENCED AFTER THE
16.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS HEARTFELT AND
OPEN WITH HIS WEDDING REGISTRY.
IS HE GOING TO LOCK IT DOWN?
LET'S LOOK AT THOSE SCORES.■■■/>
These days we're all stressed.
I hear you, sister.
Stress can affect our minds.
I call this dish, "Stress."
Stress can also affect our
bodies.
So, I'm partnering with Cigna to
remind you that your emotional
and physical health are more
connected than you think.
Go in for your annual check-up.
And be open with your doctor
about anything you feel.
Body and Mind.
Cigna. Together, all the way.
That's better.
[Happy Birthday music]
■8m>m>■;m>■,■,■■o ■=■=■)3=■
♪♪
Don't get mad,
put those years to
work with E*TRADE.
>> WELCOME BACK TO "AROUND THá■W
DECK OF PIER 17.
TONY: FOR TWO STRAIGHT YEARS,
TONIGHT IS AN ALL-TIME MOMENT IN
TH INVOL@■;■/° UCONN LOSING AND
TURN TO■CONN-NOTER AND THE
PRESSURE ONlHAT HAS BE■
AND WHAT CAN BE AND WILL BE THE
PATH TO HOW THIS ONE IS DECIDED.
BILL, START US OFF.
>> THIS COULD BE THE BEST GAME
OF ANY COLLEGE BASKETBALL
TOURNAMENT GAME, MUST-SEE TV.
I'M GOING WITH NOTRE DAME.
FOUR OF THE FIVE STARTERS WERE
ON THE FLOOR LAST YEAR AND WON
THE TITLE WITH THE BUZZER
BEATER.
WILLIAMS, FRESHMAN, ONE OF THE
BEST PLAYERS HASN'T BEEN HERE.
I GO WITH THE VETERAN.
TONY: WOODY.
>> I AGREE WITH BILL WITH NOTRE
DAME WINNING.
THE FIFTH PLAYER WAS A STARTER
TWO YEARS AGO.
COMPLETELY BETTER TEAM.
I DISAGREE WITH YOU ABOUT
WILLIAMS.
NO LONGER A FRESHMAN AND HAS
COME ON.
I GO ON WHO HAD THE GAME-WINNING
SHOT AND GOING TO BREAK THE
ALL-TIME SCORING RECORD.
TONY: HOW ABOUT YOU?
>> A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO, BUT WE
HAVE SEEN THEM FALL IN THE FINAL
FOUR AND NOTER TEAM IS SO
CLUTCH.
THEY HAVE THE EDGE OVER UCONN IN
TOURNAMENT GAMES.
IT COMES TO PRESSURE AND WHO
HANDLES IT.
AND TWO OF THE MOST CLUTCH SHOTS
IN TOURNAMENT HISTORY.
>> ALL FIVE OF THEIR STARTERS
AVERAGE IN DOUBLE DIGITS.
THEY'RE GOOD.
UCONN GOING TO DO IS SHOOTING
THREES.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING THEY CAN
DO.
TONY: BILL'S POINT THAT NOTRE
DAME RETURNS ON THE FLOOR FROM
LAST YEAR'S GAME.
UCONN RETURNS THREE.
HOW THEY BOUNCED BACK.
>> THEY WON.
TONY: WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
MOTI
IF YOU AREN'T MOTIVATED, YOU GET
IN THE MOOD.
THIS IS THE OPPORTUNITY FOR
UCONN TO ESTABLISH THE LEGACY.
OREGON AND BAYLOR.
OREGONq■■ WINS IF■ PLANK, BAYLO
WINS IF BLANCHING.
WOODY, DO YOU WANT TO WRAP YOUR
ARMS AROUND THAT?
>> SHOOTING THREE-POINTERS.
BUT THEIR BACKUP IS THE
PICK-AND-ROLL.
AND WON'T PULL IT OFF AGAINST
BAYLOR, BECAUSE THEY HAVE GIVEN
UP 22.8 POINTS PER GAME INSIDE
THE ARC.
WHEN YOU PUT THE BROWN AND COX
ON THE INSIDE, IT IS DIFFICULT
-- IF THEY PLAY WELL, BAYLOR IS
GOING TO WIN BIG.
>> THIS IS A FASCINATING GAME,
BECAUSE THEY WERE SO GOOD INSIDE
THE PAINT, 52 POINTS INSIDE THE
PAINT AGAINST IOWA.
THEY DOMINATE INSIDE.
BUT OREGON DOESN'T NEED TO
DOMINATE.
13 THREES IN THE LAST WIN.
THIRD IN THE NATION IN FIELD
GOAL PERCENTAGE.
SO THIS IS ALL ABOUT STYLE.
BAYLOR HAS POUNDED EVERYONE
BEFORE THIS.
IT WOULD BE A MIRACLE FOR OREGON
TO WIN.
>> THEY LEAD THE NATION IN
THREE-POINT PERCENTAGE, NOT WHAT
THEY DO.
41%.
ERIN IS THE KEY.
THEY MIGHT HAVE A CHANCE.
>> SABRINA IS THE BEST PLAYER ON
THE FLOOR AND I THINK BAYLOR IS
NOT CAREFUL OF DEFENDING THE
THREE-POINT SHOTS.
TONY: BUY OR SELL THREE.
WHO SAID THIS, MIKE MCCARTHY  Ry
AARON RODGERS HASN'T RESPONDED
TO THE CLAIM OF BROW BEATING AND
GRUDGE HOLDING.
WHO CAME OFF LOOKING WORSE?
>> I DON'T KNOW, YOU TELL ME.
THE GUY WHO WAS NOT TALENTED AND
I'M TAKING THE ONE THAT GOT AN
UPSIDE AND THAT IS AARON
RODGERS.
>> RODGERS FOR SURE.
HIS REPUTATION WAS NOT THE
GREATEST AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED
PUBLICLY.
THIS DOESN'T HELP ANYTHING.
I DON'T THINK ANYONE WILL
REMEMBER MIKE MCCARTY.
>> RODGERS COMES OFF AS A JERK.
THE JERK CAN STILL PLAYS.
>> MAKE IT UNANIMOUS.
RODGERS PLAYED WITH INJURY AND
MCCARTY HAS THAT ONE GREAT
MOMENT IN THE SUPER BOWL AND
OTHERWISE THOUGH HASN'T
PERFORMED WELL AS A COACH.
TONY: BUY OR SELL FOUR, RED SOX.
57 OF THE 70 INNINGS.
THEY TRAILED FOR 81% OF THE
INNINGS.
THE ASTROS-YANKEES, WORKING TO
GET WINS.
WHOSE START IS MORE OF A WINDOW?
>> THE YANKEES.
THIS IS ONLY THE SECOND YEAR.
HE DOESN'T NECESSARILY KNOW
EVERY SINGLE THING HE IS DOING.
I'M WORRIED.
>> THE CUBS.
THEY WALKED.
YOU HAVE TO GET THE BULLPEN
FIXED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HE'S GOT.
>> STARTING PITCHING WITH ONE
PARTICULAR GUY, I DON'T THINK
THE CUBS ARE OUTFITTED TO BE
EVEN THE THIRD BEST TEAM IN THAT
DIVISION.
TONY: A LOT OF MUSIC COMING YOUR
WAY, SARAH.
>> I FEEL GREAT ABOUT THE CUBS.
WHEN BILL SAYS THEY ARE IN
TROUBLE I AM NO LONGER WORRIED
ABOUT THE CUBS.
[LAUGHTER]
>> YANKEES AND TAKE THIS SMALL
SAMPLE SIZE, WE THINK THE
ORIOLES AND MARINERS ARE WINNING
IT ALL.
THE YANKEES HAVE THE MOST
TROUBLE.
INJURIES, 11-MEN ON THEIR 40-MAN
ROSTER.■■■■■■■■■
TONY: WEEKEND STARTS RIGHT NOW.
HAPPY HOUR STARTS RIGHT NOW.
YOU ARE TAKING A■C BACK SEAT.
♪♪
YOU TIRED, HUH?
NBA SUPERSTAR, HUH?
♪♪
GATORADE ZERO.■■■R■■■■
ALL THE ELECTROLYTES.
ZERO SUGAR.
GET MORE OUT OF ZERO.
The P'Zone from Pizza Hut.
It's meaty, cheesy, melty,
and you know its big.
The Pepperoni P'Zone is back
and part of the $5 Lineup.
Two or more.
Just 5 dollars
No One Out Pizzas The Hut.
óóóóI'm off to college. Mrrieet.
Don't worry.
Voya helps them to and through
retirement...
dealing with today's expenses
...while helping plan,
invest and p■he
future.■
So they'll be ok
I think they'll be fine.
Voya. Helping you to
and through retirement.
(MOM)
Ughhh
(PAUL)
You should really stop
overpaying for wireless.
(SPRINTERN)
And upgrade to the brilliant
iPhone XR with Sprint.
(SASSBOT)
Get both at Sprint for one
great price.
(BABY)
Both?
(VO)
Switch and get both an Unlimited
plan and iPhone XR lease
for just $35 a month.
For people with hearing loss,
visit Sprintrelay.com
♪♪
Introducing freedom from the
bounds of convention...
472 horses of V8
craftsmanship...
Zero to 60 in 3.96 seconds.
It's performance, born of
refinement.
The 2020 Lexus RC F Track
Edition and RC F.
Experience Amazing at your
Lexus dealer.
(Ariana)
What is he DOING?
(Vince)
He better not be messing up
our taxes.
(Lisa)
At H&R Block, you have your own
screen so you can see your
credits, deductions and tax
tips!
(Vince)
We need that now.
(Tax Pro)
What?
(Lisa VO) ♪
Know as you go at
H&R Block.
See your credits, deductions
and tax tips.
Block has your back.
Guys,
we all get to a stage
in our life
where we've earned ourselves
an upgrade.
Age sets in.
She's not as hot as
she used to be.
Should've been sent to the curb
a long time ago.
Here we go.
...to a Napoleon Grill!
Maybe I deserve the upgrade.
Good one mom.
Yeah.
Really really funny.
I thought it was funny.
When the fire goes out in your
grilling relationship,
upgrade to an.
Upgrade your grilling game.
>> HOW DO YOU SEND, LIKE ON A
PHONE?
>> YOU DON'T DO ANYTHING.
YOU READ THE EMAIL.
TONY: NEW JERSEYS?
>> I LIKE THEM.
THEY ARE GOOD LOOKING AND NEW
YORK IN THE FRONT AND SAYING WE
ARE NEW YORK.
I LIKE BEING BOLD.
>> THEY PLAY IN NEW JERSEY.
LET'S NOT GET TOO FAR CARRIED
AWAY WITH THAT.
IF YOU WANT A TREAT, LOOK UP THE
PICTURE.
[HORN]
>> I SAW THAT, TOO.
TONY: THEY ARE SAYING,■????
NEW YORK.
NEW YORK JETS.
AND HE LOOKS HIMSELF UP AND GOT
PERFECT SCORES, WORTHY OF A
PERFECT SCORE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
NOT BECAUSE OF THE JUMP■ BUT TEM
WORK ELEMENT.
YOU KNOW HOW HARD IT IS.
A-PLUS.
>> I THINK IT IS A PERFECT
SCORE.
BUT NOT THE TEAM WORK.
HE JUMPED FROM THE CROPPED
POSITION.
THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
[HORN]
TONY: HE IS 5' 9."
I DON'T KNOW WHO YOU ARE GOING
WITH.
CLINTON, SHOWDOWN, TREVOR
ROSENTHAL.
KHRIS DAVIS BATTING AVERAGE IS
ZERO.
INFINITY OR ZERO?
>> INFIPTY AND BOND BEYOND.
FOUR APPEARANCES WITHOUT A
RETIRING A BATTER.
ROSENTHAL, MUCH WORSE.
TONY: IT'S ZERO BECAUSE THE
ORIOLES ARE ABOVE .500.
THAT IS A MINOR MIRACLE.
[]tCe■■■Y&■2
TONY: TAKES THE FACE TIME.
I GIVE A SHOUTOUT TO THE TORONTO
BLUE JAYS.
IS HE TRADED?
THEY SAID, NO.
WHERE IS THIS COMING FROM?
THEY SAID LITERALLY ON THE PLUS
JAYS.
[HORN]
>> I'M GLAD YOU SAID THAT.
LAST WORD.
MY CAREER CALLING IT OUT.
I GET TO DO IT ON MY OWN.
OMITTED IT BECAUSE OF NEWS OF
THE DAY AND TIME.
NO CONSEQUENCE.
THINK PROGRESS IS COVERED.
STARTED THE CONVERSATION THAT WE
I'MTLI NOW.