CAN I HAVE A SIP OF YOUR WATER?
DAN: OH, CHRIS.
PAPI: I GOT HIM AGAIN!
DAN: PAPI, WHY DID YOU DO THAT
TO HIM?
PAPI!
CHRIS: WERE YOU IN ON THIS ONE?
YOU SAID YOU NEED SOME WATER.
PAPI, YOU NEED SOME WATER?
[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
ESPN, INC.]
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VISIT NCICAP.ORG]
TONY: TEXAS TECH-VIRGINIA.
DON'T GET SO DEFENSIVE.
REALLY, LET'S SEE IF WE CAN GET
THIS ONE OUT OF THE THE 40'S.
ALSO, BAYLOR AND NOTRE DAME,2 X
PUIG VERSUS THE PIRATES.
AUSTIN HUFF, WELL DONE.
HANG THAT AT THE LOUVRE.
>> 1940'S WITH THE BASKETBALL
GAME?
>> IT BECAME ART.
TONY: WHETHER DEFENSE SPARKS
JOY IN YOU, WHETHER IT IS FIRST
TO 50 WINS, WE WILL BREAK DOWN
VIRGINIA-TEXAS TECH IN A&=
NT.
BE THAT, WHO DOOU■X FEEL
GUILTY THINKING ABOUT AUBURN
FANS THINKING THEY WON.
HOW THE DOUBLE DRIBBLE WASN'T
CALLED, HOW THE FOUL WAS, HOW■z
THE NCAA SAYS THEY GOT IT RIGHT
WITH THE FOUL, AND THEY D
LOOK ATI@ NON-CALLS.
WE ARE GOING TOTART WITH YOU■■■
ISRAEL:■ BY LETTER OF THE  E E
OPINION, YES, THEY GOT ROBBED.
THAT WAS A DOUBLE DRIBBLE, AND
ANY HIGH QUALITY REF SHOULD BE
ABLE TO SEE IT.
ONE OF THE REFS WALKING
TRAILING THE PLAY AND SAW IT
HAPPEN IN FRONT OF HIM, BUT IT
IS SOMEONE ONE OF THOSE
SITUATIONS YOU ARE NOT
EXPECTING SOMETHING TO HAPPEN.
DID THEY GET ROBBED?
I HAVE SEEN A LOT WORSE.
THAT FOUL CALL WAS ABSOLUTELY A
FOUL.
HE BUMPED THE GUY IN THE AIR.
DOESN'T MATTER WHAT LEAGUE YOU
ARE PLAYING IN.
THAT IS GOING TO BE A FOUL.
I UNDERSTAND THE REASONING FOR
THE THING.
I AM NOT A FAN OF IT.
WHEN I THINK OF THIS GAME AND
HISTORY I DO NOT THINK OF
AUBURN GETTING ROBBED.
I THOUGHT THE FOUL AND THE
DOUBLE DRIBBLE IS SOMETHING
THAT CAN BE.
TONY:
TONY: KEVIN BLACKISTONE, CAN
AUBURN GET ROBBED?
KEVIN: NO, IT DIDN'T GET
ROBBED.
THE OTHER THING WASN'T
MENTIONED WAS THE FACT THAT
JARED HARDY WENT TO THE LINE
AND ONLY HIT 1-2.
HE -- ANOTHER GUY HIT ALL
THREE.
A GRAB ON THE JERSEY THAT WAS
NOT CALLED A FOUL.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THE
DISCUSSION ABOUT CALLING FOULS
IN THE LAST CRITICAL SECONDS OF
A GAME.
WHAT ARE REFEREES OUT THERE TO
DO?
IF THIS IS OUR CONCERN, FOR THE
LAST 60 SECONDS TAKE THE REFS
OFF THE FLOOR AND LET EVERYBODY
ON THE FLOOR CALL THE GAME
THEMSELVES.
THE CALL IN THE CORNER ON THE
CORNER WAS ABSOLUTELY A FOUL.
TONY: MINA KIMES?
MINA: I THINK THEY GOT ROBBED.
THAT WAS A FOUL.
THE DOUBLE DRIBBLE WAS A
MISTAKE.
BUT IF YOU SLOW IT DOWN AND
RE-LIT GATE EVERYTHING THAT
HAPPENS, THE AUBURN DEFENDER
DID GET A PEELS OF THE JERSEY
BEFORE THE DOUBLE DRIBBLE
HAPPENED.
WE CAN KEEP DOING THAT OVER AND
OVER.
I DO OBJECT THE NCAA COMING OUT
AND DEFENDING THE LAST CALL BUT
NOT THE DOUBLE DRIBBLE.
I THINK IT WOULD BE GOOD IF
THEY ADMITTED THEY MADE A
MISTAKE.
I LIKE IT.ONLY.
GO LOU AND ORDER ON THE SHOW.
WOODY PAIGE, WHAT ABOUT ABOUT
YOU?
WOODY: LET ME TAKE YOU BACK IN
TIME.
AFTER HARPER MISSES THE
FREE-THROW, THEY HAVE A FOUL TO
GIVE RIGHT THERE.
WHAT DO THEY DO?
THEY FOUL HIM AT THE FREE-THROW
LINE.
5.4 SECONDS REMAIN.
AT LEAST LET HIM GO TO MID
COURT OR OVER.
THEN FOUL HIM.
YOU HAVE USED UP MOST OF THE
CLOCK AND YOU STILL HAVE
ANOTHER FOUL TO GIVE AND NONE
OF THAT HAPPENS.
AUBURN WAS NOT ROBBED.
AUBURN ROBBED ITSELF OF A
CHANCE TO WIN THE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP AND DIDN'T DO IT.
THAT IS EITHER BRUCE PEARL'S
FAULT FOR NOT SIGNALING TO THEM
OR THEIR FAULT FOR NOT WAITING
UNTIL THE CLOCK ATE AWAY.
TONY: THAT IS GOOD ADVICE,
WOODY PAIGE.TONY BENNETT, I DO
AUBURN, BUT I DO FEEL BETTER
FOR ALSO.
KIND OF SAVAGE.
KYLE GUY HITTING THOSE
FREE-THROWS.
HERE IS A QUESTION.
IS IT FAIR OR FOUL TO WISH FOR
YOUR OPPONENT TO CHOKE?
THAT IMAGE OF BRYCE BROWN GOING
TO THE NECK WAS OUT THERE
IMMEDIATELY.
MINA: IT IS FAIR TO PITCH FOR
IT BUT FOUL TO DO THE CHOKING
HAND MOTION.
TONY YOU JUST DID IT.
ARE YOU WISHING THAT UPON YOUR
OPPONENT HERE?
WOODY PAIGE, FAIR OR FALL TO GO
TO THAT?
WOODY: I THOUGHT AUBURN HANDLED
IT WELL AFTER THE GAME.
BUT THIS THAT SITUATION, NO,
THAT IS UNCALLED FOR.
WE HAVE BEEN TALKING ABOUT
MAKING A CALL OR NOT MAKING A
CALL.
HE SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE IT.
TONY IT IS CLEAR YOU DON'T WANT
YOUR OPPONENTS TO HIT THE
FREE-THROWS THERE.
ISRAEL, WAS IT FAIR OR FOUL?
ISRAEL: I DON'T THINK IT IS
FAIR.
HE PROBABLY SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE
IT.
ANY TIME YOU ARE PAST 18, YOU
SHOULD PROBABLY RECOGNIZE THAT
IS NOT A GOOD GESTURE TO DO.
BUT YOU PROBABLY WANT THE GUY
SHOOTING THE FREE-THROWS TO SEE
YOU.
TONY: GOOD POINT.
BLACKISTONE.
KEVIN: IT IS FOUL.
TONY: WE MOVE ON.
TEXAS TECH GETTING IN BYING
THE AIR OUT OF THE BALL ON
MICHIGAN STATE THE LAST TWO
MINUTES AND ALSO ALL GAME LONG,
WHICH BRINGS US TO TONIGHT
THE P■í THIS IS
HISTORICALLY LOW SCORING.
THE OVER/UNDER WAS SET AT.■■■■a
SET■■■■■■■■■■■■■@■■ LOW, HOW LO
THIS BE WON?
WOODY: IT IS NOT A PROBLEM
BECAUSE THEY ARE EQUAL IN TERMS
OF HOW THEY PLAY THE GAME.
THEY BOTH HAVE MOTION OFFENSES
THAT BASICALLY HAVE COME FROM
PEEL NEWELL AND BOB KNIGHT, WHO
MENTORED BEARD.
YOU LOOK AT WHAT VIRGINIA HAS
DONE, AND THAT IS BASED ON THE
MOTION OFFENSE.
SO OFFENSIVELY THEY ARE GOING
TO TAKE TIME BECAUSE THEY ARE
PASSING THE BALL TO GET THE
BEST SHOT.
DEFENSIVELY YOU'VE GOT TWO
TEAMS THAT ARE BASICALLY THE
SAME IN TERMS OF HOW MANY
POINTS THEY GIVE UP.
ABOUT 55 PER GAME BOTH DURING
THE REGULAR SEASON AND DURING
THE TOURNAMENT.
YOU CAN THINK THAT IS GOING TO
BE AROUND 110.
TAKE THE UNDER.
BUT I THINK THAT VIRGINIA HAS A
SLIGHT EDGE BECAUSE OF THE FACT
THEY PLAY THE DEFENSE A BIT
STRONGER THAN TEXAS TECH.
ON THE OTHER SIDE, THE RED
RAIDERS PLAY TOUGHER.
TONY: WAIT, WAIT.
ONE SIDE IS STRONGER AND THE
OTHER SIDE IS TOUGHER.
DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU ARE TRYING
TO GET TO THERE.
LET'S SEE IF ISRAEL DOES.
ISRAEL: I AM NOT SURE WHAT HE
IS TRYING TO GET THERE, BUT
BOTH TEAMS ARE DEFENSIVE
POWERS.
IT SEEMS TO ME LIKE TEXAS TECH
HAS BEEN MORE DOMINANT IN
STRETCHES, WHETHER IN THE
TOURNAMENT OR JUST IN THE FINAL
FOUR.
THAT IN THE END IS WHAT IS
GOING TO LEAN ME TOWARDS TEXAS
TECH.
THE STYLES ARE SIMILAR.
VIRGINIA HAS JUST GOT A WAY TO
SLOW THE GAME DOWN.
TEXAS TECH CAN DO THAT, BUT WE
CAN SCORE A LITTLE BUILT IN
BUNCHES.
THE ONLY REASON I WOULD PICK
VIRGINIA IS TO SAY IN A CLOSE
GAME, ALL OF A SUDDEN TEXAS
TECH IS GOING TO CHOKE OR NOT
KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I DON'T BELIEVE.
THAT I THINK TEXAS TECH CAN WIN
BY DOUBLE FIGURES.
TONY: K.B., IS THAT HOW YOU SEE
IT?
KEVIN: I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT,
BUT I DON'T THINK THIS IS GOING
TO BE LIKE THE WISCONSIN TEAM
THAT ONLY PUT UP 41 IN THE 2000
FINAL FOUR.
IT IS GOING TO BE MORE THAN
THAT.
YOU HAVE SOME OFFENSIVELY
SKILLED PLAYERS WHO CAN MAKE
PLAYS.
JEROME A GINOBILI-ERVING PLAYER
FOR VIRGINIA, AND CULVER ON THE
OTHER SIDE.
MOONEY HAS BEEN HITTING CLUTCH
THREE-POINT SHOTS.
IT IS GOING TO BE A GRIND.
I DON'T THINK THAT IS GOING TO
BE A BAD CAN'T THING.
ONE THING WE ENJOY IS A TENSE
GAME.
I DON'T THINK THE DEFENSES WILL
MUCK IT UP AND MAKE IT UGLY.
TONY: MINA KIMES, YOU ARE
SMIRKING A LITTLE BIT THERE.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
MINA: WELL, IT IS POSSIBLE I
HAVE BEEN LISTENING TO TOO MUCH
OLD TOWN ROAD TOO MUCH.
I AM GOING WITH TEXAS TECH.
PICKED THEM FOR THE UPSET FOR A
CUP 8 OF REASONS.
VIRGINIA HAS BEEN THE BETTER
REGULAR SEASON TEAM, BUT TEXAS
TECH HAS BEEN BETTER IN THE
TOURNAMENT.
THEY HAVE DEFEATED A MURDERER'S
ROW OF TEAMS, INCLUDING
GONZAGA.
I THINK TEXAS TECH HAS THE BEST
NBA PROSPECT LEFT IN THIS IN
JARRETT CULVER.
HE HAS BEEN HOT AND CALLED.
HE WOULD COME UP IN THE CLUTCH.
TONY: THAT WOULD BE GOOD FOR
YOU BECAUSE YOU WOULD WIN THE
POOL ON THIS.
WOODER, WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY
STRONGER AND TOUGHER?
WOODY: TEXAS TECH HAS BEATEN
FOUR NUMBER ONE AND TWO SEEDS.
VIRGINIA WOULD BE THE FIRST
TEAM SINCE 1979 TO ACTUALLY WIN
THE TOURNAMENT WITHOUT HAVING
BEATEN A NUMBER ONE OR NUMBER
FWOFMENT
TONY: THAT IS A GOOD POINT.
AND THEY NEEDED A LOT TO MAKE
THAT HAPPEN.
TWO FOR TEXAS TECH AND TWO FOR
VIRGINIA OR IS IT 3-1?
I DID HEAR ISRAEL SAY IT COULD
BE DOUBLE DIGITS.
I AM HAPPY TO HEAR THE GAME
COULD GET INTO DOUBLE DIGITS.
MAYBE A 12-9 AFFAIR WE
FINE.
IF IT IS IN THE 40'S, MAYBE IT
WILL BE AS CLOSE AS
BAYLOR-NOTRE DAME LAST NIGHT.
THIS WAS THRILLING HOW IT
FINISHED.
INJURY TO LAU■■=■=WM■■>■1■7■zZ
TITLE WITH THE LAST YEAR
NOT BEING ABLE TO TIE IT■p UP O
THE LINE THIS YEAR.
K.B., HOW DO YOU THINK THIS
GAME WILL BE REMEMBERED, BY THE
JACKSON MAKE OR OGUNBOWALE'S
MISS?
KEVIN: IT MAY BE UNFAIRLY BY
U.S.A. BASKETBALL'S■ MISS ONLY
BECAUSE OF WHAT YOU JUST
POINTED OUT.
SHE WALKS TO THE FREE-THROW
LINE, AND YOU JUST ASSUME THAT
BOTH OF THOSE ARE GOING DOWN.
THEN SHE IS GIVEN THE ORDER TO
MISS THE SECOND ONE.
YOU DON'T PRACTICE MISSING
FREE-THROWS.
THAT MUSCLE MEMORY KICKED IN,
AND THE BALL STILL GOES IN THE
HOOP, AND THEY ARE BEHIND THE
8-BALL.
I WILL REMEMBER IT FOR CLOWE'S
GREAT LAY-UP.
SHE IS OUT OF THE WASHINGTON,
D.C. AREA.
FIRST TIME EVER PLAYING POINT
GUARD, WINS ONE FOR BAYLOR.
THAT WAS GREAT.
MINA: IN THE SHORT TERM, LUGO
ARIKE.
SHE IS PROBABLY ONE OF THE
GREATEST COLLEGE BASKETBALL
PLAYERS IN THE HISTORY OF THE
GAME.
SHE SCORED 31 POINTS, SECOND
MOST IN THE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP EVER.
UNFORTUNATELY, IT ENDED HOW IT
DID.
HOPEFULLY, JACKSON WILL BE
REMEMBERED FOR HAVING A GREAT
TOURNAMENT AND BROUGHT THIS
TEAM TO THE CHAMPIONSHIP.
TONY WOODY PAIGE?
TONY: I AM GOING TO REMEMBER IT
BECAUSE OF CLOWE.
LAUREN COX WHEN SHE WENT OUT IN
THE THIRD QUARTER, I THINK IT
CHANGED THE DIMENSION OF THE
GAME BECAUSE BAYLOR WAS ABLE TO
GET INSIDE.
AT THE VERY END THEY CALLED THE
SAME PLAY FOR CLOWE THAT THEY
DID AGAINST -- FOR CLOWE THAT
THEY DID AGAINST OREGON.
I THINK THAT PLAY MADE THE REAL
DIFFERENCE IN THE GAME AND THE
FACT THAT THEY WERE ABLE TO GET
INSIDE ALL GAME.
54 POINTS IN THE PAINT AND
NOTRE DAME ONLY HAD 24.
THAT HAS NOT HAPPENED TO THE
YEAR ALL YEAR.
TONY AND ISRAEL GUTIERREZ?
ISRAEL: IF YOU ARE GOING TO
JUDGE THIS BASED ON THE MISSED
FREE-THROW AT THE END, IT WAS
BECAUSE YOU WEREN'T WORKING.
CHLOE JACKSON WAS DOING
EVERYTHING SHE COULD.
SHE LOOKED LIKE THE QUICKEST
PLAYER ON THE COURT.
EARLIER IN THE DAY SHE ALMOST
CHOKED ON A JUMBO SHRIMP.
THAT IS AN INTERESTING DAY FOR
SOMEBODY WHO HAD TO HAVE THEIR
LIFE SAVED POTENTIALLY BY A
TEAMMATE AND THEN YOU WIN A
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP.
[HORN SOUNDS]
TONY: WE HAVE BEEN HORNED.
TAKING A BREAK.
WE WILL BE BACK WITH "BUY OR
SELL."
THIS TICKET WAS PLACED IN
NOVEMBER, TEXAS TECH TO WIN IT
ALL.
IT WOULD PAY $300,000.
MY QUESTION IS WOULD YOU HEDGE
THAT RIGHT NOW AND SETTLE UP
FOR $150,000 IF YOU COULD?
IF YOU COULD JUST WALK AWE WAY
WITH $150,000 NOW, OR WOULD YOU
LET IT RIDE AND TRY TO GET THE
$300?
YOU DON'T WANT TO ANSWER THE
QUESTION.
I THINK SOMEONE IS GOING TO LET
WE DON'T JUST MAKE CARS...
IT RID
WE MAKE TECHNOLOGY
THAT MOVES PEOPLE
♪
THIS IS THE 2019 NISSAN ROGUE
FEATURING TECH LIKE
PROPILOT ASSIST
IT HELPS KEEP YOU
CENTERED IN YOUR LANE
♪
AND IN CONTROL
THIS IS HOW NISSAN INTELLIGENT
MOBILITY IS REINVENTING DRIVING-
FOR EVERYONE.
NOW THE MOST EXCITING TECH YOU
OWN IS IN YOUR DRIVEWAY
What do you do while you
wait for that no name charcoal
to light, brother?
Arts and crafts?
Choose the charcoal
worth your flame.
Fastest lighting.
Longest burning.
For the way
barbecue should taste.
Kingsford.
■■ ;>■>;>q>■>1áq q,■,ç8ñ,ñ,ñ,■>■
Everyone at school
has the glittery one.
Of course
she wants that one.
And she wants the
one with the doodads.
No one has the one
with doodads yet.
Because no one
can find it.
For the glittery one,
and the one with doodads.
eBay.
óóó
I'm off to coll'm  retirement.
eBay.
Don't worry.
Voya helps them to and through
retirement...
dealing with today's expenses
...while helping plan,
invest a■ for theture.
So they'll b
I think they'll be fine.
Voya. Helping you to
and through retirement.
I had no symptoms
of Hepatitis C.
Mine...
...caused liver damage.
EPCLUSA treats all main types
of chronic Hep C.
Whatever your type,
ask your doctor
if EPCLUSA is your kind of cure.
I had the common type.
Mine was rare.
EPCLUSA has a 98%
overall cure rate.
I just found out
about my hepatitis C.
I knew for years.
EPCLUSA is only one
pill, once a day,
tar without
food for 12 weeks.
Before starting EPCLUSA,
your doctor will
test if you have had
hepatitis B, which may flare up
and could cause
serious liver problems
during and after treatment.■
Tell your doctor if you
have had hepatitis B
other liver or
kidney problems, HIV
or other medical conditions...4
...and■pake,
including herbal sts.
Taking amiodarone
with EPCLUSA may
cause a serious slowing
of your heart rate.
Common side effects include
headache and tiredness
Ask your doctor today, if
EPCLUSA is your kind of cure.
ANNOUNCER: WELCOME BACK TO
"AROUND THE HORN," BROUGHT TO
■■■■HASE■■■■■■
FROM THE SEAPORT DISTRICT
ANOTHER PIER 17.
TONY WOODY PAIGE HOLD ON TO
YOUR ROCKY TOP.
WE ARE GOING IN ON BARNES
BARNES HERE.
TENNESSEE -- HARRISON BARNES
RICK BARNES.
TENNESSEE OR UCLA.
BARNES SAYS HE IS GOING TO PRAY
ON IT.
WHAT DO YO OR SELL?
WOODY: THE BETTER GIG IS AT
TENNESSEE.
HE HAS GROWN IT THERE.
IT WILL CONTINUE TO GROW THERE.
UCLA HASN'T BEEN RELEVANT IN
MORE THAN 10 YEARS.
THEY HAVE WON ONE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP WITHOUT JOHN
WOODEN.
YOU WOULD HAVE TO START FROM
THE GROUND TO BUILD IT UP
AGAIN.
TONY: GOOD PIECE OF
INFORMATION, WOODY.
ISRAEL, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
ISRAEL: HE HAS ALREADY
ESTABLISHED A QUALITY PROGRAM.
YOU ARE SORT OF RESETTING AND
HAVING TO DO THE WHOLE THING
OVER AGAIN AT UCLA.
WHY?
BECAUSE THEY WON A BUNCH OF
CHAMPIONSHIPS A BUNCH OF YEARS
ACT.
COLLEGE SPORTS IS ABOUT WINNING
RIGHT NOW.
NO WHAT HAPPENED IN THE PAST.
TONY: K.B.?
KEVIN: IT IS ABOUT THE BEST
FIT.
HE HAS BROUGHT SOME STABILITY
TO A TENNESSEE BASKETBALL
PROGRAM THAT WAS IN FLUX.
IT HAS NEVER BEEN BETTER THAN
WHAT WE HAVE SEEN THIS YEAR.
LET'S NOR FORGET, HIS WIFE IS
FROM TENNESSEE.
TONY: MINA KIMES?
MINA: I AM GOING TO UCLA.
IT IS REPORTED THEY ARE
OFFERING HIM $5 MILLION A YEAR.
CHECK OUT THE TAXES SOMEONE WHO
LIVES HERE.
BUT THEY ARE DESPERATE FOR SOME
GOOD NEWS, AND I IMAGINE THEY
WOULD GIVE HIM NEGLIGENCE
COME AT THIS POINT.
TONY: IT SHOULD BE SAID THAT
THE ONE TITLE SINCE JOHN WOODEN
IS ONE MORE THAN TENNESSEE HAS.
THE WIFFLET LAST NIGHT IN
THE NBA BEFORE THE REFEREE GAVE
DION WAITERS THE BALL.
MIAMI SAYS IT COST THEM A SHOT
AT THE END OF■■EGULATION.
OVERTIME LOSS MEANS THEY ARE
CLINGING TO■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
ORLANDO, DETROIT AND ONE OTHER.
ISRAEL: THIS IS ONE OF THE
WEAKEST ARGUMENTS EVER, IF THAT
IS WHAT YOU ARE HANGING YOUR
SEASON ON.
IF THEY WANTED TO MAKE THE
PLAYOFFS.
THEY HAVE SHOULD HAVE NOT LOST
TO THE SUNS A WHILE AGO.
THEY SHOULD HAVE NOT LOST THE
THREE GAMES BEFORE THIS.
THEY HAD A LEAD IN THIS ONE.
THY DID NOT PERFORM.
KEVIN: I LOOK AT THAT PLAY AND
I AM THINKING WHAT REALLY HURT
THEN WASN'T THE WHISTLE.
IT WASN'T SPOELSTRA DOING HIS
THING.
IT WAS THE FACT THAT YOU MADE A
BAD DECISION WITH THE PASS THAT
GOT FUMBLED AWAY.
THEN YOU GOT STUCK IN THE
CORNER, HOPING SOMEBODY IS
GOING TO FOUL YOU ON A
THREE-POINT SHOT.
NOT HAPPENING.
TONY: MINA KIMES.
MINA: IF MIAMI HAD ONE WON OF
THEIR FOUR GAMES, THEY WOULD BE
IN CONTROL OF THEIR DESTINY.
IF THEY HAD HIT A SHOT THEY
WOULD HAVE WON.
TONY: WOODY PAIGE?
WOODY: ERIC HIMSELF DISTRACTED
ABOUT THE R
TONY: BUY OR SELL THREE.■■>
ZION, PLAYER OF THE YEAR.■
YOU ALL AGP■■ ARE■ HERE, DUKE L
INTO THE ALLEGATIONS FROM
MICHAEL AVENATTI OF WHETHER
ZION'S MOTHER WAS PAID BY NIKE
FOR CONSULTING SERVICES AS A
BRIBE, AVENATTI'S WORD, TO GO
TO DUKE.
WHAT DOES IT MEAN AND WHAT DO
YOU BELIEV K.B.?
KEVIN: WELL, IT MEANS THERE MAY
BE SOMETHING THERE.
BUT NOT BECAUSE MICHAEL
AVENATTI SAYS THOUGH BUT
BECAUSE WE HAVE 10 TEAM CHARGED
IN THIS COLLEGE BASKETBALL
RECRUITING SCANDAL.
CHUCK PERSON, TWO OF HIS
PLAYERS ON THE COURT FOR
AUBURN, HE IS HEADED TO JAIL
FOR 2 1/2 YEARS.
I BELIEVE THERE MUST BE
SOMETHING THERE.
TONY: MINA KIMES?
MINA: I OPENED THE 41 H- PAGE
DOCUMENT THAT HE ALLUDED TO,
AND I DIDN'T SEE ANY EVIDENCE.
I DIDN'T SEE ZION OR HIS MOM'S
NAME.
IT IS NOT A STORY FOR ME.
TONY: INSIDE P.D.F. INFORMATION
FROM MINA KIMES.
HOW ABOUT YOU WOODY PAIGE?
MICHAEL: I DON'T TRUST THE
ACCUSER, BUT HE MUST HAVE AN
VEGAS BECAUSE YOU ARE TALKING
ABOUT THE TOP COLLEGE PLAYER IN
THE COUNTRY AND GOING TO GO
NUMBER ONE IN THE DRAFT.
IF THERE IS SMOKE, YOU HAVE TO
APPLY YOURSELF TO IT.
ISRAEL: THIS ISN'T THE ACCUSED
THAT IS GOING TO POP THE LID
OFF THE INVESTIGATION AND GET
DUKE CAUSALITY RED-HANDED HERE.
IF YOU BELIEVE THERE ARE
CERTAIN SCHOOLS AND PLAYERS
HONET DO IT, YOU ARE KNIFE EVE.
TONY: DO YOU THINK THAT SOME OF
AVENATTI'S MORE FAMOUS CLIENTS
ARE LIKE I DON'T WANT TO BE
ASSOCIATED WITH ANYTHING AS
DIRTY AS COLLEGE BASKETBALL.
THERE IS A JOKE.
WE ARE GOING TO MOVE ON.
NICK SABAN GOING FOR UNDERCLASS
MEN.
>> I KNOW THERE ARE COMPELLING
STATS OUT THERE ABOUT GUYS
GOING OUT EARLY FOR THE DRAFT.
IN THE LAST FIVE YEARS, THERE
HAVE BEEN 380 PLAYERS OR THERE
ABOUTS GOOD OUT FOR THE DRAFT,
AND 25% OF THOSE GUYS DIDN'T
EVEN GET DRAFTED, AND ANOTHER
25% WEREN'T ON THE TEAM IN
THREE YEARS.
SO THAT MEANS 50% OF THE GUYS
WHO WENT OUT EARLY FOR THE
DRAFT HAD FAILED CAREERS.
TONY: MEENA, BY OR SELL?
MINA: I AM SELLING IT.
SOME PLAYER'S DRAFT STOCK
RISES, SOME FOUL.
THEY CAME OUT AND SAID ARE YOU
CARING ABOUT US OR THE PROGRAM?
WE KNOW WHAT THE PLAYERS THINK.
TONY: WOODY PAIGE?
WOODY: I AM BUYING IT, BUT PUT
SOME PEANUTS IN THAT COKE AND
SETTLE DOWN.
HE IS ADDRESSING THE PLAYERS
WITH HIM NOW SAYING STAY IN
SCHOOL BECAUSE WE WANT YOU
HERE.
TONY: SEVEN UNDERCLASS MEN
GOING PRO.
THAT IS THE MOST HE HAS SEEN.
ISRAEL: I AM SELLING IT BECAUSE
OF THE MESSENGER AS WELL.
NICK SABAN IS THE ANGEL AND THE
DEVIL ON YOUR SHOULDER.
WHEN HE IS RECRUITING, HE IS
SAYING I AM GOING TO GET YOU TO
THE NFL AS FAST AS POSSIBLE.
ON THE OTHER SHOULDER, LET NOT
HURRY AS MUCH.
COME ON.
KEVIN: ANOTHER
MULTI-MILLIONAIRE COACH TRYING
TO HOLD ON TO HIS REAMINU
AYTONNED LABOR POOL.
HE PUTS MORE PEOPLE IN THE NFL
THAN ANY OTHER TEAM.
WHAT THIS REALLY MEANS IS HE
DOESN'T WANT TO WORK AS HARD
RECRUITING ANYMORE.
R]TONY: ANYTHI■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■$
DDDD PAY STRUCTURE IN THE NFL.
WE KNOW WHAT HE WAS TALKING
ABOUT.
MEENA AND WOODY PAIGE, WE HAVE
TO SAY GOODBYE QUICK.
WE HAVE A SHOWDOWN TO GET TO
WITH ONE TOPIC.
♪♪
■■       Don't get mad,
put your money to work
with E*TRADE's easy-to-use
investing tools.
WE DON'T JUST MAKE CARS...
WE MAKE TECHNOLOGY
THAT MOVES PEOPLE
♪
THIS IS THE 2019 NISSAN ROGUE
FEATURING TECH LIKE
PROPILOT ASSIST
IT HELPS KEEP YOU
CENTERED IN YOUR LANE
♪
AND IN CONTROL
THIS IS HOW NISSAN INTELLIGENT
MOBILITY IS REINVENTING DRIVING-
FOR EVERYONE.
NOW THE MOST EXCITING TECH YOU
OWN IS IN YOUR DRIVEWAY
GATORADE ZERO.
ALL THE ELECTROLYTES.
ZERO SUGAR.
♪♪
GET MORE OUT OF ZERO.zRR■■:
I■  ■
♪trodç■8■■■■■w■■.
The pizza pepperoni fans
have been craving,■===■=2
30% more pepperonian our tradi,
over 3 signature chees■
Try all six new specialties
and get any large
for just 12 bucks.
BETTER INGREDIENTS.
BETTER PIZZA. PAPA JOHN'S.
Guys,
we all get to a stage
in our life
where we've earned ourselves
an upgrade.
Age sets in.
She's not as hot as
she used to be.
Should've been sent to the curb
a long time ago.
Here we go.
...to a Napoleon Grill!
Maybe I deserve the upgrade.
Good one mom.
Yeah.
Really really funny.
I thought it was funny.
When the fire goes out in your
grilling relationship,
Upgrade your grilling game.
>> I STAYED UP LATE.
>> WHAT WAS LATE?
>> AFTER 10:00.
TONY: KEVIN AND ISRAEL WERE
BRAWLYESTERDAY. E RED-PIRATES ç
IT WENT ON FOR TWO MND
30 SECONDS. ■■■E..<<■■■■■■BELL S
■■>■>
R THIS BRAWL TO
TWO MINUTES AND 30 SECONDS,
AND THE PHOTO OF PUIG WHICH HAS
TURNED INTO ART BY EVERYBODY.
THAT IS GORGEOUS.
WHO IS TO BLAME AND WHO IS TO
PRAISE HERE?
ISRAEL: THERE IS NOT A LOT OF
PRAISE TO GO AROUND, EXCEPT FOR
YASIEL PUIG.
HE NEEDED TO BE A DEFENSIVE
END.
DID YOU SEE HOW MANY PEOPLE
WERE TRYING TO BLOCK HIM AND
COULDN'T STAY IN FRONT OF THIS
GUY.
HE COULD GET TO ANY QUARTERBACK
IN THE NFL I GUARANTEE IT.
KEVIN: WHAT IS TO BLAME IS THE
UNWRITTEN BASEBALL RULES, YOU
HAVE TO THROW AT A GUY BECAUSE
HE STARED AT HIS HOME RUN TOO
LONG.
PITCH AROUND HIM.
DON'T LET HIM HIT A HOME RUN.
>> THEY DID PITCH AROUND HIM.
THEY PITCHED BEHIND HIM IN THIS
CASE.
>> YOU ARE GOING TO GET THE
POINT AND THE FACE TIME, KEVIN.
SOMEBODY NEEDS TO BE PRAISED.
THE ARD WORK WAS INCREDIBLE.
IT ALL  J■■WR FOR YOU,
KEVIN.
TAKE YOUR 30 SECONDS.
KEVIN: I WANT TO GIVE A SHOUT
OUT TO U.V.A. AND CARLA
WILLIAMS THE ATHLETIC DIRECTOR
THERE FOR A FEW YEARS.
SHE IS THE FIRST BLACK WOMAN TO
BE THE A.D. AS A POWER FIVE
SCHOOL, AND IT IS A GREAT
ELEVATION FOR HER.
SHE WAS AN ALL H- S.E.C. GUARD
AT GEORGIA, WORKED HER WAY UP
THROUGH THE GEORGIA PROGRAM,
THROUGH THE ATHLETIC DEPARTMENT
TO GET THIS JOB.
I AM NOT SAYING I AM ROOTING
FOR YOU -- FOR U.V.A., BUT