COMEBACKER, AND AVOID LOSING
SOME TEETH AND MAYBE HIS NOSE
IN THE PROCESS.
LOOK AT THAT.
WHAT IS THAT, AN INCH AWAY?
AND JUST LIKE NEO, MCHUGH'S
MOVE HELPS SAVE THE WORLD, OR
AT LEAST THE INNING, WITH A
DOUBLE PLAY, PROVING YOU CAN
SAVE THE GAME AND SAVE FACE AT
THE SAME TIME.
GET IT?
WELL, THAT'S IT FOR US.
I'M OFF TO TAKE THE BLUE PILL.
"NFL LIVE" IS NEXT.■■■■■■■■■x■x.
♪♪
>>> WE GOT A BIG DAY IN THE NFL
TODAY.
SCHEDULE RELEASED TONIGHT AT
8:00 EASTERN ON ESPN.
AND A PREVIEW THE FIVE
INTERNATIONAL GAMES RELEASED
TODAY.
CHECK THAT OUT, FOUR LONDON
GAMES, BEARS VERSUS RAIDERS,
PANTHERS, BUCS, TEXANS VERSUS
JAGUARS AND ON MONDAY NIGHT ON
ESPN WE HAVE NOVEMBER 18th DATE
AZTECA STADIUM IN MEXICO.
IEFS AND CHARGER F OFFqzqzqz■z■.
WELCOME TOLIVE."
ADAM SCHEFTER HERE, RYAN CLARK,
LOUIS RIDDICK AND JOINING US IN
A BIT HERE IN STUDIO, THE TOP
WIDE RECEIVER IN THE DRAFT, OLE
MISS' D.K. METCALF.
A BIG SHOW BECAUSE THE NFL DRAFT
EIGHT DAYS AWAY ALREADY.
WE ARE GETTING CLOSER.
WE HAVE TO HAVE THE KINGS ON,
MEL KIPER JR., TODD McSHAY,
THESE TWO EATING BREAKFAST
TOGETHER.
SEEM LIKE TO LIKE ONE ANOTHER.
>> GOT A BETTER OMELET THAN I
>> YOU HAVE TO BE SICK OF EACH
OTHER.
LET'S GET READY FOR NASHVILLE,
RIGHT.
THE CARDINALS HEAD THEIR PRESS
CONFERENCE ON TUESDAY.
HERE'S GENERAL MANAGER STEVE
KEIM ON WHERE THE CARDS STAND
WITH THE NUMBER ONE OVERALL
PICK.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> WE ARE NOT DONE WITH THIS
PROCESS.
WE HAVE NOT MADE A DECISION ON
THE FIRST OVERALL PICK, ALL
RIGHT.
SECONDLY, THERE ARE A NUMBER
PLAYERS IN MY OPINION AND OUR
SCOUTS OPINION AND COACHING
STAFFS' OPINION THAT WARRANT
BEING THE FIRST OVERALL
SELECTION.
HAVE WE RECEIVED CALLS ABOUT
TRADING FOR THE FIRST PICK OR
ANY OF OUR PLAYERS, THOSE ARE
THE SORT OF THINGS I'M GOING TO
KEEP PRIVATE AND IN-HOUSE.
>> RECEIVED THE FIRST PICK AND
HOW MUCH MORE DO YOU EXPECT TO
RECEIVE?
>> I'M NOT GOING TO GET INTO THE
DETAILS BUT THERE'S DEFINITELY
BEEN SOME ATTENTION.
>> YOU SAID --
>> CONVERSATIONS ANY OF THEM
CONVERSATIONS THAT GAVE YOU
PAUSE?
>> YEAH.
ERE'S ALW"F
I GET EXCITED.
I LIKE TO DO DEALS, BUT AT THE
SAME TIME I LIKE GOOD PLAYERS.
I THINK AGAIN IT GOES BACK TO
I MEANd■■NS■ YOU CAN'TN.
PASS UP AND IT'S THE NEXT THREE
DRAFTS OF SOME OF THESE TEAMS
YOU WOULD HAVE TO CONSIDER IT.
WHEN IT COMES TO THIS PRESS
CONFERENCE AND YOU GUYS THINK
THAT THIS IS MISINFORMATION, I
MEAN WE'RE NOT THE ONLY ONES
SPITTING IT OUT.
THERE'S A LOT GOING AROUND.
THE FACT THAT I DON'T KNOW WHAT
WE'RE DOING BUT EVERYBODY ELSE
DOES IS CONCERNING.
>> IS THERE A REASON WHY YOU
HAVEN'T MADE UP YOUR MIND ON THE
NUMBER ONE PICK SH.
>> BECAUSE WE HAVE TIME.
>> A YEAR AFTER DRAFTING JOSH■1
WHY YOU ARE THINKING ABOUT
DRAFTING A QUARTERBACK WAS?
>> I NEVER SAID I WAS.
>> ARE YOU NOT OPEN TO DRAFTING?
>> I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
>> LIKE HE'S UP ON THE STAND
THERE.
I THINK HE DID A FAIRLY GOOD JOB
OF TAKING ALL THOSE QUESTIONS.
>> I DON'T THINK HE ANSWERED ANY
QUESTIONS.
>> HE DIDN'T.
THAT'S WHY HE DID A GOOD JOB.
LOOK, THEY DON'T WANT TO GET
THAT INFORMATION OUT THERE.
THAT SAID, ADAM SCHEFTER, WHAT
ARE YOU HEARING ABOUT WHAT DO
YOU THINK THE CARDS WILL DO
HERE?
>> I THINK THEY LOVE QUINNEN
WILLIAMS AND I THINK THEY LOVE
NICK BOSA AND THEY WOULD BE
HAPPY TAKING EITHER OF THOSE
PLAYERS.
BUT I'M GOING TO CONTINUE TO
STICK BY WHAT KLIFF KINGSBURY
SAID LAST FALL WHICH IS THAT IF
HE HAD THE NUMBER ONE PICK IN
THE DRAFT, WHICH HE DOES, THAT
HE WOULD TAKE KYLOE■] MURRAY.
WHICH I THINK WILL WIND UP BEING
THE CASE IN THEGg END.
NOWu7AGAIN, KRAY IS
SOMEBODY THAT CAN RUN KLIFF
KI OFFENSE AND KYLER
MURRAY WOULD CREATE EXCITEMENT
IN THE DESERT.
SO■URRAY, E■$ú TEAMS CONSIDER H1
GAMBLE, EVEN THOUGH SOME TEAMS
DON'T HAVE A HIGH FIRST-ROUN■
GRADE ON HI WOULD BE THE MOST
LOGICAL PICKERE,xFá■ARDI HAVE D
THIS OFFSEASON.
DO I THINK THAT THEY WOULD LOVE
TO TAKE WILLIAMS OR BOSA?
I DO.
DO I THINK IN THE END THEY'LLÇWE
SENSE AND HAS BEEN THE SENSE AND
CONTINUES TO BE THE SENSE AND
WE'LL SEE WHAT ARIZONA DOES NEXT
WEEK.
AS THE GREAT WOULD SAY, THEY
HAVE A LASER IN ON KYLER MURRAY
RIGHT NOW.
>> I HOPE YOU'RE GOING TO BE
DOING THAT ON DRAFT NIGHT.
YOU GUYS, YOUR BODY LANGUAGE WAS
TELLING DURING THIS.
>> I JUST THINK BECAUSE THE
THING IS, THE REASON WE HEAR
ABOUT KYLER MURRAY SO MUCH IS
BECAUSE WE IN THE MEDIA TALK
ABOUT IT ALL THE TIME, WHETHER
IT'S REPORTS OR WHETHER IT'S
KLIFF KINGSBURY SAYING THINGS
AND WE'RE TRYING TO READ INTO
IT, THAT'S WHAT STARTED ALL OF
THIS KYLER MURRAY HYPE.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE BOSA AND
WILLIAMS AND ALLEN AND THESE
GUYS, THEY'RE PROBABLY BETTER
POSITIONAL PLAYERS AT THEIR
POSITION THAN KYLER MURRAY IS.
BUT KYLER MURRAY IS A
QUARTERBACK.
WE ALL KNOW HOW THIS LEAGUE
WORKS.
YOU KNOW, GUYS GETTING THESE
HUGE DEALS BECAUSE THEY PLAY THE
QUARTERBACK POSITION.
IT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT POSITION
IN FOOTBALL.
IF KLIFF KINGSBURY STANDS ON THE
TABLE AND■  ■■■y■EHE GM■0ELLS
KEIM YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS MY
GUY, THIS G■■p■■■hILL HELP ME W
I AM TYING MYSELF TO KYLER
MURRAY, THEN HE'S YOUR PICK.
BUT IF THEY WANT TO GO IN THE
SAFER SIDE AND THE DRAFT
PROCESS, THEY MAY GO AHEAD AND
PICK THE DEFENSIVE PLAYER THAT
GIVES THEM A STARTER DAY ONE AND
A PRODUCTIVE PLAYER FROM THAT
STANDPOINT.
>> I THINK CUP TEXT IS IMPORTANT
WHEN LOOKING AT THIS PICK.
WHEN YOU HAVE A NEW HEAD COACH
GIVEN WHAT HIS TRACK RECORD HAS
BEEN AND WHERE HE'S COME FROM TO
GET TO WHERE HE'S GOTTEN WITH
WHICH I'M SURE KLIFF IS SAYING
HOW DID I FIND MYSELF TO BE THE
HEAD COACH OF THE CARDINALS
GIVEN WHERE MY CAREER WAS GOING
BEFORE THIS HAPPENED, IF I'M HIM
I'M SAYING I DON'T CARE WHAT
YOU'VE DONE IN THE PAST OR
PICKED IN THE PAST, I DON'T CARE
ABOUT JOSH OR ANYBODY, I WANT MY
PEOPLE AND IF■a■a I BELIEVE THA
KYLER MURRAY IS THE NUMBER ONE
PICK IN THIS DRAFT AND I THINK
HE WILL HELP ME GET THIS PROGRAM
GOING AND GET US GOING IN THE
RIGHT DIRECTION, THAT'S WHERE I
WANT TO GO.
IF YOU'RE STEVE KEIM YOU WOULD
BE SMART TO DO THAT.
YOU UNDERSTOOD WHAT HIS PROFILE
WAS WHEN YOU HIRED HIM AND
UNDERSTOOD WHAT HE WOULD NEED TO
BE SUCCESSFUL AND YOU KNOW THAT
QUARTERBACK COACHES/HEAD COACHES
WANT THEIR GUYS.
>> LOUIS.
>> --
>> YOU KNOW THE FRONT OFFICE, IF
YOU'RE STEVE KEIM, REMEMBER IN
THE INTERVIEW PROCESS AFTER THEY
GOT RID OF STEVE WILKS LAST YEAR
AND SAID THEY MADE A MISTAKE.
DO YOU THINK THIS WILL GIVE THAT
LEEWAY AND LEVERAGE TO GET HIS
GUY?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, QUITE HONESTLY
I DON'T KNOW ANYONE IN ARIZONA
SHOULD BE STICKING THEIR CHEST
OUT BEING LIKE I GOT ALL THE
ANSWERS AND I CAN FIGURE IT ALL
OUT.
THEY'VE PROVEN THEY CAN'T.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M SAYING THIS, IN THE WAY
THAT YOU KIND OF LIKE MAKE THOSE
DECISIONS WHEN TALKING ABOUT THE
NUMBER ONE OVERALL PICK AND NEW
HEAD COACH, COMMON SENSE WILL
TELL YOU YOU DON'T WANT TO FORCE
ANYTHING ON A HEAD COACH THAT HE
DOESN'T WANT, BUT AT THE SAME
TIME AS A GM YOU'RE TRYING TO DO
WHAT'S BEST FOR THE LONG-TERM
FUTURE OF THE CARDINALS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG THE LONG
TERM IS FOR THIS REGIME, GIVEN
THE TURMOIL THAT'S THAT IT'S
UNDERGONE.
>> IF THEY TAKE THE QUARTERBACK
IT GIVES THEM THE BEST CHANCE
FOR LONG-TERM SUCCESS --
>> AND MAYBE --
>> THE QUARTERBACK COMES IN AND
PLAYS WELL, THEY'RE SET FOR THE
NEXT 12, 15 YEARS.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> AND IF KYLER MURRAY IS THE
GUY, THEN THE INTERESTING
QUESTION OF THIS DRAFT ISN'T WHO
ARIZONA TAKES OR WANTS BUT WHAT
DO THEY DO WITH JOSH --
>> I WILL GO BACK TO SAYING
THIS, WHEN KLIFF WAS INTRODUCED
AND MICHAEL BIDWELL WAS TALKING
AND WHY DID HE HIRE KLIFF KINGS
BURY, HOW EXCITING THAT OFFENSE
WAS AT TEXAS TECH AND WANTED
SOME OF THAT ON HIS FOOTBALL
TEAM.
>> RIGHT.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> I'M SURE YOU SAW --
>> QUINNEN WILLIAMS FIRST
OVERALL.
>> RIGHT.
>> I'M SURE YOU GUYS SAW, TOO,
THAT HIS AGENT, ACCOMPANIED HIM
OUT TO ARIZONA WHICH --
>> STEVE KEIM -- HE WAS THERE IN
ARIZONA.
>> HE WASN'T IN THE FACILITY.
>> NOT IN THE MEETINGS.
>> YOU KNOW.
>> HE WAS A PART OF IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO TO MEL KIPER JR. AND
TODD McSHAY HERE.
YOU HEARD STEVE KEIM.
THE CARDINALS HAVEN'T MADE UP
THEIR MINDS AND A NUMBER OF
PLAYERS, WHAT SCENARIOS COULD
PLAY OUT AT THE TOP OF THE DRAFT
ONE WEEK FROM TOMORROW?
>> I STILL THINK THAT KYLER WILL
BE THE GUY.
IF YOU HIRE KLIFF AND WANT THE
BEST POSSIBLE QUARTERBACK FOR
HIS SYSTEM AND I THINK IT'S
KYLER, AT NUMBER ONE.
IF IT'S IN THE FOR SOME RUN,
THEN YOU HAVE TO START TO LOOK
AT THE PICTURE HERE.
THE JETS DON'T HAVE A SECOND
ROUND PICK.
AS YOU CAN SEE HERE, THEYoOI
FROM PICK THREE TO 68.
THEY'RE ONE TEAM THAT MIGHT WANT
TO MOVE OUT IF A TEAM IS LOOKING
TO MOVE UP TO THAT SPOT TO GO
GET KYLER IF HE'S AVAILABLE AT
THREE.
THE RATDSERS, I T■>ó>ó>■>■8■>■>
THE DRAFT CAPITAL WITH FOUR, 24,
27, 35, TO MOVE UP AND GO GET
HIM I WANT TO.
AGAIN I THINK THEY WOULD STAY
HOME,ÑÑ■■■[■[■[■[■z?=■z■z■[■=■[
THAT THERE'S SOME QUESTIONS
ABOUT THAT RELATIONSHIP, BUT I
THINK KYLER AT FOUR WOULD MAKE
SENSE IF THAT'S THE ROUTE THAT
JOHN WANTS TO GO.
I DON'T KNOW THEY'RE GOING TO
PACKAGE A BUNCH OF PICKS TO GET
HIM, MEL.
>> YOU SAY ALL THIS NOW BECAUSE
YOU WANT JOSH ROSEN TO HAVE
VALUE AND TALKING UP THAT PICK
LIKE WE DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
DOING -- THEY KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
DOING.
>> NO VALUE IN SAYING ANYTHING
ELSE.
>> THEY KNOW WHAT THEY WANT.
THEY KNOW THE QUARTERBACK
THEY'RE MOVING FORWARD WITH.
THEY KNOW IT.
WHETHER RIGHT AFTER THE DRAFT GO
TO CONFESSION, YOU KNOW WHY, A
LOT OF LIES THIS TIME OF YEAR.
THEY KNOW WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
JOHN DORSEY KNEW HE WAS TAKING
BAKER MAYFIELD TWO MONTHS BEFORE
THE DRAFT, DIDN'T SAY IT AN HOUR
BEFORE, BUT THEY KNOW.
MURRAY GOES ONE, IT FLOWS THE
WAY WE THINK.
THE TALK ABOUT QUINNEN WILLIAMS
AND JOSH ALLEN, NICK BOSA, GO BY
THE BOARDS.
THE RAIDERS I DON'T THINK AT
FOUR ARE TRADING UP.
IF HE FALLS MAYBE FINE.
MAYBE MIAMI WOULD BE INTERESTING
TO SEE IF THEY WOULD JUMP UP IF
MURRAY DIDN'T GO ONE.
THE DOLPHINS FEEL AT 13, TANKEN
FOR TWO, I DON'T BUY THAT, GET
THE QUARTERBACK THIS YEAR.
SCENARIOS COULD UNFOLD IF MURRAY
DOESN'T GO NUMBER ONE.
WE THINK HE WILL.
>> ALL THE ANSWERS RIGHT THERE.
>> SCHEFTER IS WHISPERING OVER
HERE LIKE CRITIQUING YOUR PICKS
ALREADY.
>> QUINNEN WILLIAMS, YOU GUYS,
YOU MENTIONED HIM.
HE'S GOING TO BE ON THE SHOW
TOMORROW.
TUNS OF QUESTIONS FOR HIM.
BY THE WAY, IF THE CARDINALS
DRAFT KYLER MURRAY HE WILL BE
THE SECOND TEAM TO DRAFT A
QUARTERBACK IN THE FIRST ROUND
IN BACK-TO-BACK DRAFTS SINCE
THE '82 AND '83 COLTS.
STILL TO COME, WE'VE GOT A JAM
PACKED D ON■ "NFL LIVE."■7■1
OLE MISS WIDE RECEIVERD.J.
METCALF IN STUDIO, WE WILL TALK
TO HIM ABOUT THE DRAFT PROCESS
AND WHERE HE THINKS HE WILL WIND
UP GOING.
PLUS, LATER IN THE SHOW, PLENTY
OF QUARTERBACKS CHANGE TEAMS
THIS OFFSEASON.
WHO WILL HAVE THE BIGGEST IMPACT
ON THEIR NEW TEAM■■■■w=LM ROOM
TAPES AND TODD, DD, TODD, DO
YOU HAVE ANY MUS
OH, MY GOODNESS.
TODD.
STOP STUDYING AND HIT THE GYM.
[Soldier Chatter] Bandit three,
this is fox two three
can you see that contact
to our front?
Bandit, fox two three alpha,
we're marking 'em
with tracer fire.
There are those who choose
a different path in life.
[Soldier Chatter] Contact.
Contact front.
A path of selflessness...
of service.
A path that leads to freedom.
[Soldier Chatter]
Lay down suppressive fire!
DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES?
Find out at goarmy.com/warriors
Scribe, take this down.
People have been left to wonder
what ingredients are in
their beer.
I shall put an ingredients label
on every case of Bud Light!
That was really great,
did you get that?
Oh. Was I supposed to be writing
that down?
Bud Light.
Now with an ingredients label.
>>> THE MUSIC CITY, WHERE STARS
ARE BORN.
A NEW GROUP OF HOPEFULS IS
WAITING IN THE WINGS.
D.K. MET CALF IS ONE OF THE MOST
INTERESTING PROSPECTS IN THIS
DRAFT.
>> THE HEIGHT/WEIGHT/SPEED
COMBINATION IS SOMETHING SCOUTS
DROOL OVER.
>> HIS FATHER WAS AN OFFENSIVE
LINEMAN IN THE NFL.
>> MY SON WAS BUILT, PRESSING 50
POUNDS AND SQUATTING 100 POUNDS
AT THE AGE OF 5 YEARS OLD.
>> FIRES DEEP, HE■■X HAS IN MET
CALF DOWN THE SIDELINE TO THE
END ZONE, TOUCHDOWN.
>> PRACTICING, PERFORMING.
>> HE'S A >> HE A FREAKISH■//7 .
WHAT A GRAB BY D.K. METCALF.
>> HE TURNED HEADS AT THE
COMBINE.
>> 6'3", 228, RUNNING A 4.33.
NOT A LOT OF GUYS LIKE THAT.
>> TURN ON THE BRIGHT LIGHTS,
PULL BACK THE CURTAIN, IT'S
TIME.
>> AFTER ALL IS SAID AND DONE HE
SHOULD BE IN THE TOP TEN OF THE
DRAFT.
MYSELF AS THE BEST((HHHH■H■ DR.
I'M NOT HERE TO PLAY GAMES.
I'M HERE TO WIN.
>> HERE'S THE THING, THE CAMERAS
THEY DON'T EVEN REALLY CAPTURE
HOW LARGE OF A MAN YOU ARE
THERE.
HERE'S WATCHING WITH MY EYES
HERE, QUITE INTIMIDATING.
THE WIDE RECEIVER D.K. MET CALF,
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR HANGING
OUT WITH US.
MY THOUGHT WAS, MAN, HE'S IN
BRISTOL ALL DAY LONG DOING ALL
THESE THINGS, FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO MAKE HIM COMFORTABLE AND
DIDN'T WANT TO GO TO THE GYM
BECAUSE I DON'T LIKE TO WORK
OUT, I FOUND OUT YOU LIKE
STRAWBERRY MILK, WHICH I FEEL
LIKE IS AN EARLY 1980'S THING.
TOO YOUNG TO LIKE STRAWBERRY
MILK.
WHY DO YOU LIKE THIS?
>> STARTED MY FRESHMAN YEAR.
I COULDN'T GO TO SLEEP SO I
WOULD GO TO THE GAS STATION AND
GET A BOTTLE OF STRAWBERRY MILK
AND PUT ME RIGHT TO SLEEP.
>> PREMADE OR POWDER.
>> PREMADE.
>> IS THIS PART OF YOUR DIET?
>> I HAD TO TAKE IT OUT WHILE I
WAS TRAINING.
>> YOU'RE OLD ENOUGH TO SIP
AFTER I GRILL YOU WITH THESE
HARD QUESTIONS.
JUST IN TERMS OF SOCIAL MEDIA A
RIGHT, WE ALL KNOW THE PICTURES.
WE'VE SEEN THEM ALL A MILLION
TIMES.
YOU WITH YOUR SHIRT OFF.
IT'S BECOME YOUR IDENTITY OF HOW
PEOPLE KNOW YOUR NAME, HOW IT
GOT OUT THERE.
WHAT WAS YOUR REACTION TO DO
REACTION THE WORLD WHEN THEY SAW
THAT PHOTO?
>> WELL, ONE OF THE QUARTERBACKS
AT OLE MISS WAS THE FIRST PERSON
WHO LET ME KNOW LIKE DUDE, YOU
ARE NOT THAT BIG.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT.
I'VE BEEN THE SAME SIZE SINCE
YOU LAST SAW ME.
REALLY, PEOPLE LOOKING AT THE
PICTURE AND LIKE BEING LIKE OH,
MY GOD, HIS ARMS, LIKE I MEAN
IT'S RIGHT NOW --
>> YOU KNOW YOU'RE BIG.
YOU DON'T POST A PICTURE IF YOU
DON'T KNOW YOU LOOK BIG.
DID YOU EXPECT IT TO GET AS MUCH
ATTENTION AS IT'S GOTTEN IN THE
PROCESS?
>> NO.
I ALWAYS KNEW I WAS BIG.
I DON'T GET WHY PEOPLE ARE
LIKE -- ALWAYS SAYING SOMETHING
ABOUT IT IN THE MEMES AND ALL
THAT.
>> SEE, I'VE NOTICED YOU DON'T
REALLY POST THAT MUCH ANYMORE OF
YOU WITHOUT YOUR SHIRT, WHICH IS
SUCH A WEIRD WAY TO GET INTO
THIS, WHY DON'T YOU POST ABOUT
IT?
>> I FEEL LIKE I DON'T NEED TO
SHOW OFF MY BODY.
>> IN TERMS OF HOW YOU WANT
TEAMS TO VIEW YOU, BECAUSE LOOK,
IT'S FRONT OF MIND FOR FANS AND
COACHES, MANAGERS, OR GENERAL
MANAGERS THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
KNOWN FOR, IF YOU WANTED THEM TO
KNOW WHAT YOU WANT TO BE KNOWN
FOR WHAT WOULD THAT BE?
>> MY GAME FILM.
BEING PHYSICAL, GO DEEP WHENEVER
I■■■ WANT TO, AND JUST GO OVER
TOP OF THE DEFENDER.
>> SPEAKING OF PHOTOS, YOUR FEL
POSTED A PICTURE SAYING YOU TWO
WOULD BE BIGGER THAN JARVIS
LANDRY AND ODELL BECKHAM, JR.
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT TWO ELITE
WIDE RECEIVERS WHO ARE
TEAMMATES.
DO YOU ACTUALLY BELIEVE THAT YOU
GUYS COULD BE BETTER THAN THEM?
>> I KNOW THE WORK A.J. PUTS IN
SINCE WE GOT TO OLE MISS.
IT WOULDN'T BE A SURPRISE TO ME.
>> YOU KNOW MAKING COMPARISONS
TO RECEIVERS LIKE THAT, I MEAN
THAT'S PUTTING YOURSELF OUT
THERE BECAUSE YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT REALLY GOOD GUYS.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT YOUR SPECIFIC
GAME THAT YOU THINK YOU COULD BE
IN CONVERSATIONS WITH?
PLAYERS LIKE ODELL BECKHAM, JR.?
>> I TRY TO MODEL MY ROUTE
RUNNING GAME AFTER THEM, BUT ONE
PERSON I REALLY WATCH IS JULIO.7
>> WHAT DO YOU LIKE ABOUT JULIO?
>> HE'S 6'3" AND CAN BREAK A
ROUTE DOWN LIKE 5'10".
>> WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE ROUTE TO
RUN?
GO.
>> WHY IS THAT?n■a BY THE DEFEN
SPEED.
>> WE KNOW WE SHOWED A LITTLE
BIT OF VIDEO OF YOUR FATHER
THERE.
HE PLAYED IN THE LEAGUE.
WE KNOW AT H THEY'RE
AT WORK WATCHING  BUT WHAT
KIND OF GUIDANCE HAS HE GIVEN
YOU THROUGH THIS PROCESS LEADING
UP TO THE DRAFT?
>> JUST ENJOY THE MOMENT AND
CONTINUE TO WORK HARD.
EVEN WHEN I GET THERE, JUST
CONTINUE TO BE THE SAME PERSON
WHO I AM.
THE HARD-WORKING KID FROM
MISSISSIPPI.
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT.
HE KNOWS HOW HE RAISED ME AND HE
RAISED ME REAL WELL.
I THANK THEM■kók]k■k■k]kókók]kós
JUST WORK HARD AND BE NICE TO
PEOPLE.
>> BE NICE TO PEOPLE.
DO YOU FIND THAT DIFFICULT WHEN
GOING THROUGH THIS PROCESS?
BECAUSE IT'S -- THE EXPERIENCE
IS SO DIFFERENT THAN ANYTHING
ELSE YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH?
>> IT'S KIND OF HARD.
>> DO YOU EVER WANT TO YELL AT
TODD McSHAY WHEN HE HAS YOU
FALLING OR MEL KIPER JR. SAYING
YOU AREN'T GOING TO GO IN THE
FIRST FIVE PICKS, DO YOU WANT TO
GO YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT?
>> I KNOW THEY'RE JUST DOING
THEIR JOB.
CAN'T BE MAD AT THEM.
EVERS HAS THEIR OPINION OF WHERE
I'M GOING TO GO OR LAND, BUT
IT'S JUST THEIR OPINION.
>> LOTS OF US SAW IN INDY AT THE
COMBINE AFTER YOU RAN THE
FASTEST 40 FOR YOUR WEIG
WERE REALLY EMOTIONAL.
WHAT MADE YOU SO EMOTIONAL ABOUT
THAT MOMENT?
>> I MISS MY FAMILY FIRST OFF
AND THEN JUST ACCOMPLISHING LIKE
SEEING ALL MY HARD WORK GETTING
PAID OFF.
IT WAS -- THEN MY MOM TOLD ME
SHE WAS PROUD OF ME.
THAT'S REALLY WHAT BROKE ME
DOWN.
>> YOU'RE EMOTIONAL RUNNING THE
40, THE FASTEST ONE, SO WE
UNDE■ YOU WERE
EMOTIONAL ABOUT IT.
NOW HERE WE ARE, EIGHT DAYS AWAY
FROM THE DRAFT.
WHAT'S IT GOING TO BE LIKE WHEN
YOU HEAR YOUR NAME CALLED?
>> IT'S GOING TO BE GREAT.
SPEND THAT DAY, THAT TIME WITH
MY FAMILY, JUST BEING AROUND
THEM, AND, YOU KNOW, JUST SEEING
ALL MY HARD WORK PAY OFF WITH
THEM WATCHING.
>> ALL THE PEOPLE IN YOUR LIFE,
THIS IS HARD, SOUNDS LIKE YOU
HAVE A GREAT FAMILY, WHO IS THE
ONE PERSON THAT WHEN YOUR NAME
GETS CALLED YOU WANT TO MAKE
SURE THEY KNOW YOU'RE SO
GRATEFUL FOR EVERYTHING THEY DID
FOR YOU?
>> MY MOM.
>> YOUR MOM.
WHY?
>> SHE RAISED ME.
MY TWIN, MY DAD SAYS WE'RE JUST
ALIKE, SO JUST TO SEE THE SMILE
ON HER FACE WHEN MY NAME GETS
CALLED IS GOING TO BE GREAT.
>> THAT'S AN EARLY MOTHER'S DAY
PRESENT YOU CAN GET MOM.
>> THANK YOU.
>> CONTINUE DRINKING.
HANG ON.
WE'RE GOING TO PUT YOU THROUGH
OUR "NFL LIVE" COMBINE COMING
UP.
YOU'RE JUST GETTING WARMED UP
HERE.
STILL TO COME, KIRK COUSINS
FIRST YEAR IN MINNESOTA.
NOW HE'S COMPARING PREP FOR THE
SEASON TO EATING AN ELEPHANT.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THAT MEANS.
BUT WE'RE GOING TO TRY TO
EXPLAIN IT COMING UP NEXT.
PLUS, BRONCO'S QUARTERBACK JOE
FLACCO SPOKE TO REPORTERS BUT HE
DOESN'T WANT THE BRONCOS TO DO
SOMETHING.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> THAT'S NOT OF MOST IMPORTANCE
TO DRAFT A QUARTERBACK.
ñ1■#x#■#■
We're Carvana,
the company who invented
car vending machines and buying
a car 100% online.
We're Carvana,
the coo
■Now we've created a brand new
way for you to sell your car.
Whether it's a year old
or a few years old,
we want to buy your car.
So go to Carvana
and enter your license plate,
answer a few questions,
answ questions,
and our techno-wizardry
calculates your car's value
and gives you a real offer
in seconds.
When you're ready,
we'll come to you,
spot,
ck up your car.
pay you on the spot,
and pick up your car.
That's it.
So ditch the old way
of selling your car,
and say hello to the new way--
at Carvana.
(mker)f mud, gravel,
and trail dust.
For the love of
roads, ds,
and no roads.
For the love of
hunting, fishing,
and working the land.
For love of conservation,
for kicking up American soil.
TRACKER Off Road.
So...
Built for love of country.
You're driven, and you have
a ton of goals...
But you're stuck in the vicious
cycle of credit card payments.
It's time to get a personal
loan from SoFi.
Borrow up to $100k to pay off
your credit cards,
and then pay us back with
one monthly payment.
And it's all with zero fees.
Get a personal loan,
and pay no fees.
♪
>>> IN A DRAFT ROCKING WITH PLAY
MAKERS, TEAMS IN NEED OF A
QUARTERBACK ARE SEEKING A HIT
MAKER.
AND THESE THREE ARE MAKING
EVERYONE LISTEN.
THE NFL DRAFT BEGINS APRIL 25th
ON ESPN AND ABC.■8■8■■%
BACK HERE ON "NFL LIVE" ON
THIS WEDNESDAY.
VETERAN WIDE RECEIVER DAMARIOUS
THOMAS HAS A NEW HOME IN NEW
ENGLAND.
BACK IN 2010 McGAHNEN WAS A HEAD
COACH OF DENVER AND DRAFTED■v
THOMAS.
THE 31-YEAR-OLD ONCE PRODUCED
FIVE CONSECUTIVE 1,000-YARD
SEASONS.
WILL HE MAKE THE PATRIOTS 53-MAN
ROSTER?
WE'VE SEEN THE PATRIOTS PICK UP
VETERAN PLAYERS AND WHETHER THEY
MAKE IT COME AUGUST, THAT SAID,
HOW DID THIS COME TOGETHER?
>> THIS IS A SITUATION I DON'T
THINK HE HAD A LOT OF INTEREST
OUT THERE.
WHEN SITTING ON THE FREE AGENT
MARKET IN MID-APRIL AND LOOKING
FOR A HOME, THAT TELLS YOU THAT
YOU DIDN'T HAVE THE MARKET THAT
INJURY.UGHT COMING OFF THE
THAT'S NOT A SURPRISE.
NEW ENGLAND IS IN A POSITION
WHERE IT WAS LOOKING TO ADD
OFFENSIVE HELP.
IT NEEDS OFFENSIVE HELP.
IT HAS LOST SO MUCH THE LAST
COUPLE YEARS.
BRANDIN COOKS, DANNY AMENDOLA,
ROB GRONKOWSKI.
WHO IS GOING TO COME IN AND
REPLACE THEM RIGHT NOW?
BECAUSE OF THAT, YOU NEED PEOPLE
TO STEP IN AND DO THE JOB AND
DEMARYIUS THOMAS AS YOU
MENTIONED WAS DRAFTED BY JOSH
McDANIELS AND NOW THE PATRIOTS
OFFENSIVE COORDINATOR.
IT SHOULDN'T BE HARD FOR
DEMARIUS TO LEARN THE SYSTEM AND
ASSUMING HE'S UP TO SPEED THEY
BELIEVE HE CAN CONTRIBUTE TO
SOME OF THAT OFFENSE THIS
SEASON.
>> THAT'S THE BIGGEST THING, HOW
DOES HE COME BACK OFF THIS
INJURY.
LOOK AT HIS PRODUCTION AT THE
BEGINNING OF LAST YEAR WITH THE
DENVER BRONCOS, IT WAS DOWN,
CASE KEENUM WASN'T PLAYING A
HIGH LEVEL OF QUARTERBACK AND HE
GOES TO HOUSTON, HUGE FIRST GAME
AGAINST THE DENVER BRONCOS, THEY
TARGET HIM EARLY AND MAKE SURE
HE GETS THE BA ANDADES AWAY■)■
UNTIL THE INJURY.
THAT'S ANOTHER PIECE TO NOT
HAVING A HUGE MARKET FOR
DEMARYIUS THOMAS.
HE IS UBER TALENTED, A BIG BODY
THAT CAN GET THE BALL.
IF HE'S HEALTHY AND ABLE TO
PRODUCE LATE IN THE SEASON THAT
WILL BE WHAT THE NEW ENGLAND
TS HAVE TO BE LOOKING FOR
WHEN INTO THE PLAYOFF
STRETCH, DOWN LATE FOOT SEASON,
IN DECEMBER, EARLY JANUARY, CAN
DEMARYIUS THOMAS BE A PIECE FOR
THAT?
I DON'T SEE HIM BEING A GUY WHO
CONTRIBUTEHO IS R AT
THE BEGINNING OF THE SEASON.
U THINK HE MAKES THIS
ROSTER COME AUGUST?
>> YOU KNOW ■■■■■■, I THINK AS
LONG AS HIS HEALTH PLAYS OUT I
THINK HE DOES.
THIS IS CLASSIC TEAM BUILDING.
THIS IS CLASSIC VALUE PLAY,
CLASSIC VALUE SHOPPING, LOW
RISK/HIGH REWARD, WHAT NEW
ENGLAND DOES.
WE'LL FIND A GUY WE KNOW CAN HIT
THE GROUND RUNNING, NOT GOING TO
LOSE A LOT FROM NOT BEING ON THE
FOOTBALL FIELD BECAUSE HE HAS
FAMILIARITY WITH OUR OFFENSIVE
COORDINATOR FROM HIS TIME IN■v■
DENVER.
IT'S MATTER OF CAN WE GET HIM
HEALTHY AND ON THE FIELD AND
KEEP HIM ON THE FOOTBALL FIELD.
BECAUSE WE DON'T -- WE'RE NOT
LOOKING FOR HIM TO BE A GUY A
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN-YEAR PLAYER,
WE'RE LOOKING FOR SOMEONE AT
OTHER POSITIONS OTHER THAN
QUARTERBACK YOU HAVE BRIDGE
PLAYERS, PLAYERS THAT BUY YOU
TIME UNTIL YOU CAN KIND OF
RESTOCK THE CUP BOARD.
IT'S CLASSIC FOR NEW ENGLAND.
MOST PEOPLE GO, DEMARYIUS
THOMAS, GOING TO BE 32 YEARS
OLD.
FOR WHAT?
FOR THEM THEY GO WE'LL TAKE THAT
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
MAKES SENSE FOR THEM.
>> LISTEN, $150,000 SIGNING
BONUS.
IF THEY'RE WRONG, SO WHAT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
IF THEY'RE RIGHT, THEN THEY'RE
THE PATRIOTS.
>> AREN'T THEY ALWAYS RIGHT.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
>> WHEN IT COMES TO VETERAN
PLAYER ACQUISITION, THEY KIND OF
DO IT BETTER THAN ANYONE.
>> THEY DO.
>> THEY FOLLOW REALLY THE THINGS
THAT LEAD YOU TO SUCCESS,
FAMILIARITY WITH YOUR SYSTEM,
FAMILIARITY WITH THE PLAYERS.
HERE IT'S A MATTER OF HELP WHICH
IS BIG BUT YOU'RE RIGHT $150,000
GAMBLE.
>> IT'S IRONIC, THEY CUT PLAYERS
THAT ARE ABOUT TO BE TOO OLD,
BUT THEN THEY BRING BACK OLDER
PLAYERS AND MAKE IT WORK.
>> USUALLY IT'S BECAUSE THOSE
PLAYERS THAT THEY DO CUT, THEY
KNOW MORE ABOUT THEM THAN ANYONE
DOES OR GETTING TOO PRICEY, OR
THEY THINK THAT THEY DESERVE
MORE.
>> THAT'S USUALLY THE HUGE
THING, THEY'RE GETTING PRICEY
AND IT'S NOT WORTH THAT PRICE
FOR US.
>> WORTH $150,000.
>> THEY NEED HELP ON OFFENSE.
THEY'RE NOT DONE YET.
THEY NEED MORE HELP.
>> BILL HAS A CLASSIC LINE,
SOMETHING TO THIS EFFECT, WE
DON'T PLAY ANY GAMES ANY■v■ ■nI
SOON.
LAST I CHECKED.
SCHEDULE --
>> IT'S COMING OUT TONIGHT ON
ESPN 2 AT 8:00.
LOOKING FORWARD TO YOUR
REDIXIONS HERE IN APRIL BEFORE
THE DRAFT.
>> I WANT TO PREDICT THE
REDSKINS TWO 16-0 I WAS WRONG.
>>OU MENTION BRIDGE PLA IN
TERMS OF WHAT THE PATRIOTS ARE
DOING.
YOU HAVE TO WONDER IF JOE FLACCO
WILL BE A BRIDGE QUARTERBACK FOR
THE TEAM.
IF IT WAS UP TO JOE,■■■■■■■■■■■
DOES NOT WANT THE DENVER BRONCOS
TEAM TO DRAFT A QUARTERBACK.
WE KNOW WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM IN
BALTIMORE W■1f7 RAVENS.
TAKE A LISTEN TO HIS THOUGHTS ON
WHAT THE BRONCOS SHOULD BE
DOING.
>> I WANT TO GET THIS TEAM TO BE
THE BEST IT IS WITH ME AT THE
QUARTERBACK POSITION.
OBVIOUSLY THAT'S NOT THE MOST --
OF MOST IMPORTANCE TO DRAFT A
QUARTERBACK, BUT IF WE DO,
THAT'S COMPLETELY OUT OF MY
CONTROL.
I'M GOING TO GO OUT HERE AND
COMPETE AND HE'S GOING TO HAVE
TO COME OUT AND BE ON THE FIELD
WITH ME EVERY DAY TOO.
I'M READY FOR THAT.
IF WE FEEL AS A TEAM AND
ORGANIZATION WE CAN ADD VALUE
WITH A TENTH PICK I'M ALL FOR
GETTING A GUY THAT CAN ADD VALUE
TO THE TEAM WITH ME AS THE
UNDERSTOOD QUARTERBACK.
>> I LIKE THE COMMENTS.
THROWING OUT THERE, LIKE LOOK --
>> LIKE A SCORNED LOVER.
>> I'M TELLING YOU, THIS IS ONE
OF THE SITUATIONS WHERE WHEN
PEOPLE START MOCKING DWAYNE
HASKINS OR ANY OF THESE YOUNG
QUARTERBACKS, IF I'M ONE OF
THOSE QUARTERBACKS I'M GOING
PLEASE DO NOT TAKE ME.
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
>> I AGREE.
>> I'M TELLING YOU, THAT RIGHT
THERE IS A SIGN THAT I'M NOT
GOING TO GET MUCH HELP IN THE
QUARTERBACK ROOM.
IT'S GOING TO BE TENSE.
>> WE HAVEN'T SAW HIM LAST YEAR
PROVIDE --
>> AS YOU KNOW --
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
>> I AM NOT READY TO MENTOR.
WE TALK ABOUT CONTEXT AND
SITUATIONS THAT ARE NOT TARE
MADE FOR QUARTERBACKS TO
SUCCESS, A QUARTERBACK WHO HAS
NEVER CALLED PLAYS BEFORE, I'M
GOING -- HEY, NO DISRESPECT TO
DENVER, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT'S
COMING NEXT.
IF I'M A QUARTERBACK I DON'T
WANT TO COME THERE.
I DON'T.
>> I LIKE JOE'S STYLE.
WANTS HIS JOB.
>> THE THING IS, THOUGH, WHEN
YOU HAVE■ó■ f/■/■■■■■ ñEñE■ñ/WA
UNDERSTAND YOU DON'T DESERVE TO
BE THE ONLY QUARTERBACK THERE.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOUR PLAY
HASN'T WARRANTED YOU THE RESPECT
THAT YOU ARE OUR GUY.
YOU HAVEN'T DONE THE THINGS IT
TAKES TO BE THE UNQUESTIONED
LEADER AND STARTER OF THIS TY
■■■■ DO ROOKIE.
SO WHAT HE'S SAYING IS HEY,"
GUYS, BUILD AROUND ME.
I CAN DO IT.HE'S BASICALLY OUT
MPAIGNING.
>>■■P;■  PROJECTING THIS.
>> DON'T QUESTION --
>> HE'S PLAYING --
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> HE'S PLAYING THE GAME TO SAY
OH, TO MAKE JO>; SAY MAYBE
WE SHOULD BUILD AROUND HIM AND
GET HIM A WEAPON AND ADD
SOMETHINGENSE B HE
DOESN'T WANT THE COMPETITION
EVEN MORE THAN THAT, DOESN'T
WANT TO HELP A YOUNG GUY TAKE
HIS POSITION LIKE HE SAW LAST
YEAR IN BALTIMORE.
>> AND LET ME SAY THIS ALSO, YOU
ARE NOW IN A DIVISION WITH
PATRICK MAHOMES AND PHILIP
RIVERS AND A RAIDER OFFENSE THAT
ADDED BROWN AND WILLIAMS.
>> AND QUARTERBACK --
>> AND MAYBE A QUARTERBACK SOON.
WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT REMAINS TO BE
DETERMINED.
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS, IN A
FAST, COMPETITIVE AFC WEST YOU
PROBABLY NEED DEFENSIVE HELP AND
THE STRENGTH OF THIS DRAFT IS ON
THE DEFENSIVE SIDE AND THE
DEFENSIVE LINE.
SOME ON THE OFFENSIVE LINE.
TO ME DENVER THINKS IT'S GOT A
GOOD TEAM.
DENVER THINKS IT CAN BE
COMPETITIVE.
TO ME DENVER THINKS IT'S GOING
WITH ONE OF THE POSITIONAL
PLAYERS TO HELP SHUT DOWN --
>> THIS TEAM HAS TO SCORE POINTS
AND PUT THE BALL IN THE AIR.
PHILIP LINDSEY CAN'T DO
EVERYTHING.
THEY HAVE A YOUNG, UNPROVEN WIDE
RECEIVER CORPS WITH ANOTHER GUY
COMING OFF --
>> COMING OFF OF --
>> WHO THERE'S A LOT OF QUESTION
ON THE OFFENSIVE SIDE OF THE
BALL.
I'M NOT SAYING QUARTERBACK IS
THE POSITION THAT WOULD HELP
THEM ADD VALUE AND FIRE POWER TO
THEIR TEAM IMMEDIATELY, BUT IT'S
NOT JUST DEFENSE.
>> YOU BETTER BE ABLE TO SCORE.
>> HOW MANY TIMES DO THEY GET TO
MISS ON THIS POSITION.
IF YOU LOOK AT THIS TEAM WITHOUT
PEYTON MANNING FALLING INTO
THEIR LAP --
>> PLENTY OF TIMES IF YOU'RE
JOHN ELWAY.
>> THIS IS FOR JOHN.
>> YOU CAN DO THAT.
>> WHEN I THINK DENVER FOR
WHATEVER REASON I THINK GARY
KUBIAK, BUT GARY KUBIAK NOW IN
PALESTINE MN AND KIRK COUSINS
GETTING HELP THERE ON OFFENSE AS
HE'S THE ASSISTANT HEAD COACH
AND CONSULTING.
KIRK COUSINS KNOWS HE HAS TO BE
BETTER AND TWEETED ABOUT THE BIG
PLAYBOOK HE'S STUDYING AND IT'S
A THICK BOOK.
TAKE A LISTEN TO HOW HE
APPROACHES LEARNING THIS
PLAYBOOK AND GETTING READY FOR
THE SEASON.
>> THE SAME WAY YOU EAT AN
ELEPHANT ONE BITE AT A TIME,
RIGHT.
YOU JUST START ON PAGE 1 AND
FLIP THE PAGE ONCE YOU FEEL YOU
■
THROUGH AND GET YOUR WITH
QUESTIONS ANSWERED.
ST YEAR THIS WEEK I WASí ■■■■■
BECARE ARE PARALLELS AND
CARRYOVER FROM THE PREVIOUS
YEARS OF OFFENSE, WITH THE ONE
WE'RE IN NOW THIS YEAR, I DO
THINK IT'S MUCH QUICKER SPITTING
THE PLAYS OUT IN WEEK ONE OF THE
OFFSEASON PROGRAM AND I THINK
THAT'S GOT TO HELP LOOK, WHEN Y
MUCH MONEY YOU DON'T EAT HAM
BURRERS, YOU EAT ELEPHANT.
>> SEEMS LIKE THAT WOULD BE
REALLY GAMEY.
>> TASTES LIKE CHICKEN, LIKE
EVERYTHING ELSE.
JUST LISTEN TO KIRK AND KNOWING
THAT HE NEEDS TO BE BETTER, HIS
TEAM WANTS HIM TO PERFORM
BETTER, DO YOU THINK THAT THIS
IS GOING TO BE A BETTER SEASON
FOR KIRK?
>> I THINK KIRK IS KIRK.
RIGHT.
LIKE LAST SEASON WAS MUCH LIKE
EVERY OTHER SEASON WE'VE EVER
SEEN FROM KIRK COUSINS AND I
EXPECT THIS SEASON TO BE MOR
THE SAME.
HE'S A GUY THAT'S GOING TO
COMPLETE A HIGH PERCENTAGE OF
PASSES.
HE'S A GUY WHO IS GOING TO
PROTECT THE BALL FOR THE MOST
PART.
HE'S ALSO IS NOTf■
GOIN BIG GAMES AGAINST
OTHER TOP CALIBER QUARTERBACKS.
WE'VE SEEN THIS YEAR IN AND YEAR
OUT WITH KIRK COUSINS.
COUSINS WAS BOUGHT -- WAS
BROUGHT TO MINNESOTA FOR ONE
REASON AND ONE REASON O
THEY THOUGHT HE WAS AN UPGRADE
TO CASE KEENUM THAT WOULD GETÑ■
THEM OVER THE HUMP INTO THE
SUPER BOWL.
WHEN THIS IS A TEAM THAT DOESN'T
GET A CHANCE TO COMPETE IN THE
TOURNAMENT.
THAT WAS LARGELY BECAUSE OF KIRK
COUSINS AND THAT DEFENSE
STARTING TO FALTER DOWN THE
STRETCH OF THE SEASON.
KIRK IS GOING TO GODO WHAT HE'S
DONE ALL THE TIME, HAVE TWO
RECEIVERS ON THE OUTSIDE AND A
TIGHT END THAT CAN REALLY MAKE
PLAYS.
WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT CAN HE
MAKE THE BIG PLAYS LATE IN THE
SEASON AGAINST OTHER TOP
QUARTERBACKS.
>> LET ME TELL YOU AN ADVANTAGE
HE HAS THIS YEAR THAT HE DIDN'T
HAVE LAST YEAR.
LAST YEAR TONY SPO RAN NO PASSED
AWAY.
I THINK IT IMPACTED THAT TEAM,
IMPACTED THEIR ENTIRE SEASON AND
THIS YEAR THEY'VE GONE OUT AND
HIRED GARY KUBIAK AND BROUGHT
ALONG RICK DENISON AND THEY'RE
GOING TO HAVE BETTER PLAY UP
FRONT AND I THINK THEY'RE GOING
TO DRAFT OFFENSIVE LINE HERE AND
THEY'RE GOING TO TRY TO SOLIDIFY
THAT POSITION BETWEEN THE
COACHING AND BETWEEN THE TALENT
THEY HAVE.■@I THINWILL BE B@@
FRONT.
BECAUSE OF ALLT I BELIEVE
KIRK COUSINS WILL BE BETTER THIS
YEAR WITH A BETTER OFFENSIVE
LINE AND A SECOND-YEAR IN THAT
ORGANIZATION.
>> AND THAT SPO RAN NO THING IS
A REAL THING.
THEY DENIED IT BECAUSE THEY WERE
IN SEASON.
POSTSEASON THE FIRST THING
ALMOST EVERY POU
THEY ALL SAID GO BACK TO AUGUST.
WHEN WE LOST TONY IT CHANGED.
>> THEY'RE IMPLEMENTING A NEW
TYPE OF RUNNING GAME.
A ZONE BLOCKING TEAM.
HA RIGHT PROFILE PLAYERS
UP FRONT.
MOVING I BACKWARDS TO KIRK,
KIRK IS NOT THE GUY WHO IS GOING
TO WIN GAMES FOR YOU.
HE'S GOING TO WIN GAMES BECAUSE
OF THE STRONG MULTIPLES.
HE'S PROVEN THAT.
DO NOT THINK KIRK'S NUMBERS AND
THINK HE IS A DIFFERENCE MAKER
OF THE PEDIGREE OF AARON
RODGERS, OR DREW BREES.
HE'S NOT THAT GUY.
JUST LOOK AT HIS NUMBERS AND
MANY TIMES WHEN WE'RE NOT
PLAYING GAMES AND WE LOOK AT
NUMBERS, JUST LIKE --
>> BEFORE HE WENT THERE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> >> PEOPLE ARE LIKE IT'S HE'S
A DIFFERENCE MAKER, TEN TIMES
BETTER THAN CASE KEENUM AND MEAN
ALL THE DIFFERENCE IN THE WORLD.
HE'S NOT.
BUT HE WAS PAID IN A WAY THAT HE
WAS.
YOU KNOW, THE KIND OF PACKAGING
WAS SET THAT WITH HIM NOW, HE'S
GOING TO MAKE THE DIFFERENCE.
HE'S THE DIFFERENCE HE BETWEEN
BEATING THE EAGLES AND LOSING TO
THE EAGLES IN THE NFC
CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
THAT'S NOT A KNOCK AGAINST HIM.
THAT'S WHO HE IS.
THEY BETTER FIX THE OFFENSIVE
LINE.
THEY COULDN'T RUN THE BALL A
LICK.
THE DEFENSE NEEDS TO REMAIN
STRONG AND MAYBE PLAY BETTER AND
TURN THE BALL OVER AND GIVE HIM
MORE SHOTS AND BE MORE BALANCED.
A LOT OF TEAMS ARE HAVING TO WIN
THIS WAY.
KIRK IS NO DIFFERENT.
HIS SALARY IS DIFFERENT THAT'S
ALL.
>> ANOTHER BITE AT THAT IN A FEW
YEARS.
THAT NUMBER GOES UP.
YOU CAN'T REALLY GAUGE ON THAT.
THAT'S --
>> ONE BITE AT A TIME.
>> THAT'S A MARK WE KNOW.
>> STILL TO COME ON■■Q■H■ --
>> BITE OF THE ELEPHANT.
THAT'S WHY Y THE BIG GUY
AROUND HERE.
>> SOME OF THE BIGGEST
QUAR NAMES THAT CHANGED
TEAMS THIS OFFSEASON.
WHICH PLAYER W HAVE THE
BIGGEST IMPACT■■■■IS NEW TEAM.
HOT TAKES COMING ■h
RUSS■■[ F■■ GOT THAT
CONTRACT EXTENSION HE WAS
LOOKING FOR AND LET US KNOW IN A
KIND OF WEIRD WAY.
>> HEY, SEATTLE, WE GOT A DEAL.
>> GO HAWKS.
♪ ♪ ♪
BECAUSE MY BODY CAN STILLY A1C.
MAKE ITS OWN INSULIN.
AND I TAKE TRULICITY ONCE A WEEK
■
TO ACTODY
TO RELEASE Ij
ô
LI■■■■■PPy>z>■>y>TRULICITY IS N.
AND I TAKE TRULICITY ONCE A WEEK
IT STARTS ACTING IN MY
BODY FROM THE FIRST DOSE
AND CONTINUES TO WORK
WHEN I NEED IT, 24/7.
TRULICITY IS AN INJECTION
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
DON'T USE IT AS THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES,
OR IF YOU HAVE TYPE 1 DIABETES
■
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
'T TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU OR YOUR FAMILY
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YONYOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY■■Y, E
IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS OF A
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTION,
Gó7■7■7óóó?7?7?7?7VV■ó?7?7?7?7?,
OR SEVERE STOMACH PAIN.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS MAY
INNCREATITIS.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN
INCREASES YOUR   BLOOD S.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEAEA, VOMITING,
ABDOMINAL PAIN, AND
CREASED APPETITE.
THESE CAN LEDRATION,
■■
WHICRSEN
KIDNEY PROBLEMS.
CHOOSE ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY
TO ACTIVATE MY WITHIN.
IF YOU NEED HELP
LOWERING YOUR A1C,
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
Travel and dining
just go together.
Now KAYAK and OpenTable
let you earn travel rewards
every time you dine.
With just one reservation
on OpenTable,
you can start saving money
on hotels with KAYAK.
Get started at
KAYAK.com/diningrewards.
-Here e rain
[ Horn honking ]
[ Engine revving ]
What's that, girl?
Flo needs help?!
[ Engine revving ]
Take me to her!
Why aren't we taking roads?!
Flo.
[ Horn honking ]
-Oh. You made it.
Do you have change for a dollar?
-This was the emergency?
[ Engine revving ]
Yes, I was busy!
From America's number-one
motorcycle insurer.
hink yobest friend.busy!
You don't have to say
I'm your best friend.
That's okay.
You don't have to say
I'm your best friend.
♪Lean on me, when you're not
strong.♪
♪And I'll be your friend.♪
♪I'll help you carry on.♪
♪Lean on Me.♪
Verizon got us VIP tickets
three feet away
from Justin Timberlake.
And to say VIP
is an understatement,
because I sawww
Justin Timberlake.
So he literally looked
into the phone
and started dancing--
well, he was already dancing--
locked eyes
and continued dancing.
Every now and then, I'm like,
"Wait, did that happen?"
(gasps)
I've got photos of it,
it must have.
(VO)
Get more music on us
with Verizon Up,
the rewards program
that gets you VIP tickets
to the best concerts and more.
Plus, save big when you switch.
Only on Verizon.
>>> FILM ROOM IS BROUGHT TO YOU
BY VERIZON, THE BEST UNLIMITED
IS ON VERIZON, AMERICA'S MOST
AWARDED NETWORK.
>>> WELL, MAYBE YOU FORGET,
WE'RE KEEPING TRACK FOR YOU, A
BUSY OFFSEASON FORQUARTERBACKS,
THROUGH THE LEAGUE TRADING CASE
KEENUM AND TRADING FOR MVP JOE
FLACCO.
WE TALKED ABOUT HIM EARLIER.
IN MIAMI, RYAN TANNEHILL'S
CAREER WITH THE DOLPHINS IS
OVER.
HE'S BEEN TRADED TO THE TITANS.
TANNEHILL PLAYED 11 GAMES LAST
SEASON, 35.4G WQBR.
HOW ABOUT RYAN FITZGERALD.
HE SIGNED A TWO-YEAR DEAL WITH
THE DOLPHINS.
THIS WILL BE FITZPATRICK'S
EIGHTH TEAM.
THE JACKSON CUT THE CORD WITH
BLAKE BORTLES WHO THREW THE MOST
INTERCEPTIONS SINCE ENTERING THE
LEAGUE IN 2014.
HE JOINS THE RAMS, GOING TO BACK
UP JARED GOFF.
BORTLES BACKUP, FOLES, SIGNED AN
$88 MILLION, JOINS HIS FORMER■8
■p■p■p■■■ ■ ■ú■ú■ú■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■P
ACTION OUT OF FOLES.
HERE'S FOLES YESTERDAY WHEN HE
SPOKE AT PRACTICE.
>> TRUST IS SOMETHING YOU CAN'T
RUSH.
THAT'S WHY YOU COME IN HERE AND
YOU STAY.
I DON'T TRY TO BE ANYTHING OTHER
THAN MYSELF.
I THINK GUYS RESPE THAT.
WHEN THEY STEP IN THE HUDDLE
WITH ME THEY'RE NOT GOING TO BE
■ DIFFERENT IN THE LOCKER ROOM
@■@■ILITY.
GOAL IS TO BE WHO I AM ALL
THE TIME.
WE'RE HERE TO MAKE THINGS BETTE
SUCCEED, BUT TO DO THAT YOU HAVE
TO BUILD A FOUNDATION AND THAT'S
TRUST.
YOU GET AN OPPORTUNITY TO KNOW
THE GUYS AND BUILD THAT TRUST
AND GROW FROM THERE.
>> LET'S HOP INSIDE THE FILM
ROOM BROUGHT TO YOU BY VERIZON.
LOUIS AND RYAN.
WE LISTED A LOT OF QUARTERBACKS
THERE BUT IN TERMS OF LONG-TERM
GAIN AND CONTRACT, NICK FOLES
PROBABLY HAVING THE BEST
SITUATION THERE.
AND, YOU KNOW, WE TALK A LOT
ABOUT HIM BEING REUNITED WITH
FLIP, BUT DO YOU ACTUALLY THINK
THEM BEING TOGETHER IN THIS
OFFENSE IS GOING TO HELP FOLES?
>> I THINK IT CAN'T HURT.
THE FAMILIARITY WILL BE KEY WITH
NICK.
YOU SAW THE GRAPHIC ABOUT HOW HE
WAS IN PHILADELPHIA WHEN WITH
PEOPLE WHO HE'S COMFORTABLE WITH
AND THEN THE CULTURE THAT MAKES
HIM OR ALLOWS HIM TO BE WHO HE
IS, VERSUS BEING SOMEWHERE WHERE
HE'S NOT.
THAT'S HUGE WITH HIM
IS JLL■8   TWO @HE FOO■■FIEL TH@
THINGS FROM NICK, THEY7■ ■ T OU
HANDS QUICKLY AND INTO PLAY
MAKERS AND THEY NEED HIM TO MAKE
GREAT DECISIONS AND NOT THROW IT
TO THE OTHER TEAM.
THE GUY WHO HAS BEEN QUARTERBACK
ON THIS TEAM DOESN'T DO A QUICK
JOB OF KEEPING IT AWAY FROM THE
OTHER TEAM.
THAT'S THE THING FIRST AND
FOREMOST ON THE FOOTBALL FIELD
THAT NICK NEEDS TO BRING AND
BRING A SENSE OF CALM TO THIS
TEAM AND LEADERSHIP TO THIS TEAM
THAT PEOPLE RESPECT AND THEN IF
YOU KIND OF LIKE EXPAND IT OUT A
LITTLE BIT, THE REST OF THE
PEOPLE IN JACKSONVILLE'S ROSTER
NEED LOOK, LET'S SLOW DOWN WITH
THE INDIVIDUAL STUFF AND KIND OF
TAKE A TOTAL TEAM APPROACH TO
THIS KIND OF THING.
THAT'S WHAT THIS KID BRINGS.
THAT'S WHAT THIS YOUNG MAN
BRINGS.
THAT'S WHAT NICK'S VALUE IS.
IF EVERYONE ELSE CAN FALL IN
LINE WITH THAT, THIS IS A TEAM
THAT WAS A COUPLE PLAYS AWAY
FROM THE SUPER BOWL.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I THINK THAT'S THE HUGE THING
WITH NICK FOLES, HE GIVES YOU A
LOT OF THE THINGS THAT BLAKE
S DIDI ALSO THAT
CONFIDENCE THAT NICK FOLES CAN
S WHEww■ THEY NEEDED TO BEE■s
DONE.
THAT'S WHAT THIS TEAM WAS
LOOKING AT G■#■W■W■W■W
SEAS
JACKSONVILLE JAGUARS THOUGHT
THEYN THE CUSP OF BEING A
SUPER BOWL
CHAMPION A■% THEN THEY RE-SIGNE
AND HE'S BASICALLY THREW THE
GAMES AWAY, LITERALLY AND
FIGURATIVELY.
SO TO HAVE A GUY LIKE NICK FOLES
WHO MAKES GOOD DECISIONS, YOU
CAN BE CONFIDENT ABOUT AT THE
QUARTERBACK POSITION IS HUGE FOR
THIS TEAM THAT FEELS LIKE THEY
HAVE PIECES OUTSIDE OF NICK
FOLES TO COMPETE IN THE AFC.
>> I WAS IN PHILLY YESTERDAY,
SPORTS TALK RADIO, CALLERS
SAYING THEY SHOULD NEVER HAVE
LET NICK FOLES GO AND HE SHOULD
BE IN PHILADELPHIA.
LEAVING QUITE THE MARK THERE IN
PHILADELPHIA.
THIS HAPPENED YESTERDAY AFTER úú
THE SHOW.
REALLY HAVEN'T HAD A CHANCE TO
TALK TO YOU ABOUT YOUR REACTION
TO THE DEAL.
DO YOU THINK RUSSELL WILSON
DESERVED THIS AMOUNT OF MONEY TO
PLAY IN SEAT UNTIL.
>> DESERVE IS A SUBJECTIVE WORD.
THIS IS WHAT THE MARKET DICTATES
FOR A GUY WHO HAS PUT■=■7■7■>é;B
HIS NUMBERSNG TO BE 2 BOW#p
SURPASSED QUICKLY WHEN THE NEXT
THE SALARY CAP IS RISING AND THE
MONEY IS THERE.
THAT'S WHAT THE MARKET IS.
YOU CAN ARGUE THIS IS A RUN
CENTRIC OFFENSE A'T
DESERVE THIS, DOESN'T CARRY
INFLUENCE ON THIS OFFENSE LIKE
DREW DOES IN NEW ORLEANS OR
WHATEVER.
OT THE■ HERE.
WHAT'S YOUR NEXT BEST
ALTERNATIVE OUTSIDE OF RUSSELL?
>> 100%.
>> I KNOW RIGHT NOW WE'RE IN THE
TIME OF YEAR WHERE SCOUTING
RIGHT NOW --
>> YOUNG QUARTERBACK --
>> WE CAN ALL IDENTIFY.
COME ON, GIVE IT A BREAK.
SEATTLE RIGHT NOW DID THE RIGHT
THING AND MAKE SURE THEY ARE
JUDICIOUS HOW THEY DIS PERCENT
THE REST OF THE SALARY CAP.
NOT EVERYBODY WILL BE ABLE TO
GET PAID.
LIKE EVERY TEAM THAT HAS A FRIZ
QUARTERBACK NOT EVERYBODY CAN
GET PAID.
THAT MEANS WHERE THERE IS NO
SALARY CAP, COACHING, SCOUTING,
DEVELOPMENT, PUMP SOME MONEY
INTO THAT AND MAKE SURE YOUR
PROGRAM IS TIGHT AND STRONG AND
CAN WITHSTAND PAYING A GUY LIKE
THIS.
YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW WHAT LIFE
IS LIKE WITHOUT HIM, I CAN TELL
YOU THAT.
>> THE SEATTLE SEAHAWKS GOT BACK
TO BEING THEM LATE IN THE SEASON
WITH CARSON RUNNING T L1■@
FOOTBALL, HAVIN■■ RUSSELL WILSO
MAKE HUGE PLHE FIELD,
TO LOCK IT.
$ LOO■ AT WHAT THEY WERE
DIFFERENT THAN WHAT&t[■#IT.
RUSSELL WILSON WAS CARRYING THIS
TEAM.
THEY WERE BAD UP FRONT, COULDN'T
RUN THE BALL, CONSTANTLY UNDER
PRESSURE AND HE FOUND WAYS TO
GET THOSE TEAMS AND THAT TEAM
OUT BAD SITUATIONS WITH HIS
PLAY.
YOU'RE GOING TO LOOK AT THE
NUMBERS AND IT'S NOT GOING TO BE
AARON RODGERS' NUMBERS AND HE'S
NOT GOING TO THROW THE BALL
AROUND THE FIELD LIKE WE'VE SEEN
SOME OTHER TOP QUARTERBACKS DO,
BUT FOR WHERE HE SITS ON THIS
TEAM AND WHAT HE DOES AND WHERE
THE MONEY IS BEING SPENT, HE
DESERVED EVERY PENNY HE GOT.
THE SEATTLE SEAHAWKS AND MR.
SNYDER UNDERSTOOD THAT AND
THAT'S WHY HE GOT THIS DEAL.
>> SEATTLE, WE GOT A DEAL.
THAT'S WHAT HE SAID FROM HIS BED
WITH HIS BEAUTIFUL -- SOUNDS SO
WEIRD TO SAY ON TELEVISION BUT
THAT'S WHAT HE POSTED ON HIS
INSTAGRAM.
WE SAW IT WITH HIM AND SIERRA
CELEBRATING.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S COOL, BUT IT
IS KIND OF WEIRD, VERY PERSONAL.
WELL, HIS TEAMMATES, OF COURSE,
THEY HAD THEIR OPPORTUNITY TO DO
THEIR BESTSSION OF WHAT
RUSSELL WILSON POSTED.
CHECK THIS OUT.
>> HEY, SEATTLE, WE GOT A DEAL.
>> GO HAWKS.
>> THIS WHAT I LOVE ABOUT IT.
RUSSELL WAS A COOL SPORT ABOUT
IT.
LOOK --
>> JUST GOT 140.
I WOULD BE A COOL SPORT TOO.
>> IF I'M CIARA I'M MAD ABOUT
THAT IMITATION.
DO YOU SEE HER IN THAT LIGHTING
AT NIGHT.
SHE'S PERFECT.
>> THAT'S WHY IT'S FUNNY BECAUSE
IT'S DJ --
>> THAT'S GOOD STUFF.
THE FACT THEY CAN GET ALONG LIKE
THAT.
I'M NOT SURE IF ALL QUARTERBACKS
HAVE THAT GREAT OF HUMOR LIKE
RUSSELL WILSON.
>> CONGRATS TO HIM AND HIS
FAMILY.
>> STILL TO COME, D.K. METCALF
BACK IN HERE, SOME OF THE HARD
S HE MAY HAVE HEARD
DURING TEAM INTERVIEWS AND WE
WILL TAKE HIM THROUGH SOME OF
HIS BEST PLAYS ON THE FIELD IN
COLLEGE AND A LITTLE TODD McSHAY
AND MEL KIPER JR.
>> THAT IS HARDER THAN IT LOOKS
THOUGH.
I'M NOT VERY GOOD AT IT.
>> I DID IT DURING THE FANTASY
SHOW AND WENT TEN FOR TEN.
IT'S NOT THAT HARD.
WE'LL BE
(Client's Voice)
Remember that degree
you got in taxation?
(Danny)
Of course you don't
because you didn't!
Your job isn't
understanding tax code...■■
it's uo=ng why t■;■■■■■■■
will get him a body like that...
MOVE!
...that.
Your job isn't
do work...
Here.
...it's making
her do hard work...
...and getting paid for it.
(VO)
Snap and sort your expenses to
save over $4,600 at tax ti
(Danny)
Jody...
...it's time to get yours!
(VO)
QUICKBOOKS. BACKING YOU.
♪♪
Ready to de nation.
Ready to fight for
what matters.
No mat.
DO YWHAT IT TAKES?
Find out at goarmy.com/warriors
>>> BIGGEST NAMES IN THE DRAFT,
THREE NIGHTS ONLY, DROPPING THE
GREATEST HITS LIVE FROM
NASHVILLE.
THE NFL DRAFT BEGINS ON ESPN AND
ABC.
>> WELCOME BACK TO "NFL LIVE."
WE HAVE OUR FIRST ROUND DRAFT
PROSPECT ON THIS WIDE RECEIVER
D.K. METCALF IN STUDIO ALL DAY
LONG.
HE WILL BE AT THE DRAFT NEXT
WEEK IN NASHVILLE.
YOU KNOW, SO WE KNOW THAT YOU'VE
BEEN THROUGH WEEKS AND WEEKS OF
PREP LEADING UP TO THIS AND WE
GOT TONS OF QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS
PROCESS FOR YOU.
WE FIGURED WE WOULD COME UP WITH
OUR OWN "NFL LIVE" COMBINE IN A
WAY, SORT OF REPLICATE WHAT
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH.
WE KNOW ONE OF THE BIGGEST PARTS
AND PROBABLY THE MOST IMPORTANT
PART OF THIS PROCESS IS HOW YOU
COME ACROSS TO GMs AND COACHES
AND TO THESE ORGANIZATIONS.
IT'S THE OFFICIAL INTERVIEW
PROCESS.
HERE'S OUR LOUIS RIDDICK.
OBVIOUSLY WAS PLAYER.
A PRETTY GOOD ONE I HEAR.
ALSO HE WAS IN THE FRONT
OFFICE --
>> OVERRATED.
>> MEL DID SAY YOU WERE
OVERRATED.
>> YEAH.
HE WAS IN THE FRONT OFFICE WITH
THE EAGLES AND REDSKINS.
KIND OF EMULATE AND TAKE YOU
THROUGH WHAT YOU PROBABLY FACE.
SO LOU, WHAT'S YOUR BIG QUESTION
FOR D.K.?
>> THERE'S A NUMBER OF QUESTIONS
PEOPLE HAVE ASKED YOU ABOUT YOUR
PERSONAL LIFE TO YOUR PEDIGREE
AS FAR AS PEOPLE WHO PLAYED IN
THE PROS BEFORE YOU.
I WOULD WANT TO ASK YOU, IS
INJURIES.
YOUR INJURY HISTORY.
YOUR NECK INJURY, IS IT
SOMETHING YOU FEEL AS THOUGH
WILL AFFECT YOU GOING FORWARD AS
FAR AS YOUR -- THE WAY YOU PLAY
THE GAME AND APPROACH THE GAME?
IS THERE ANY KIND OF RESERVATION
DO YOU HAVE ABOUT IT AND DO YOU
FEEL TOTALLY HEALTHY AT THIS
POINT GOING FORWARD?
>> YES, SIR MY INJURIES ARE
FREAK INJURIES THAT COULD HAVE
HAPPENED TO ANYBODY AT ANY TIME
IN THE GAME.
I GOT CLEARED TO PLAY FULL
CONTACT ON JANUARY 21st.
>> THIS IS ANOTHER THING PEOPLE
WILL ASK YOU ABOUT AS FAR AS HOW
YOU PLAY THE GAME ON THE
FOOTBALL FIELD.
YOU'RE A BIG WIDE RECEIVER NOW,
ALMOST 230 POUNDS, 6'3", 6'4".
AS FAR AS THE SIZE IS CONCERNED,
I USED TO LOVE BEING IN THE
WEIGHT ROOM AND PUMPING IRAN
IRON LIKE YOU.
THERE COMES A POINT YOU GET TOO
BIG.
IS THAT SOMETHING YOU'VE THOUGHT
ABOUT PLAYING WIDE RECEIVER IN
THE NFL.
IT'S GOOD TO BE BIG AND STRONG
AND RUN THIS WAY.
YOU HAVE TO BE ABLE TO RUN THIS
WAY, CHANGE DIRECTIONS.
IS THAT SOMETHING YOU GOT YOUR
EYE ON TO MAKE SURE YOU'RE NOT
GETTING TOO BIG?
>> NO, SIR.
I'M GOOD.
MY WORKOUT PLAN AND I'M A
RECEIVER FIRST.
I KNOW CHANGING DIRECTION IS NOT
GOING TO BE A PROBLEM FOR ME.
>> GOOD.
THOSE ARE QUESTIONS I WOULD WANT
TO KNOW.
>> YEAH.
I WAS NERVOUS DURING THAT WHOLE
THING.
IS IT NERVE-RACKING WHEN IN
THESE INTERVIEWS?
>> I'M USED TO THEM.
>> YOU'RE USED TO THEM.
>> COMES FROM A GREAT PEDIGREE.
>> I WILL BE A SHAM CHAPERONE OR
MAYBE YOUR AGENT.
TAKE YOU THROUGH THESE STATIONS.
COLLEGE FILM WITH TODD AND MEL.
THEY STUDY THIS ALL YEAR-ROUND.
THEY'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU WHAT
THEY SEE ON TAPE AND WE WANT TO
GET YOUR REACTION TO IT.
>> GOING TO ASK YOU A QUESTION
FIRST.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> YOU SAY JULIO JONES IS YOUR
GUY.
>> RIGHT.
>> WHAT AREAS OF YOUR GAME NEED
TO IMPRO■■@■@@@■J GET TO THAT P
ONCE YOU'RE IN THE NFL.
>> GETTING IN AND OUT OF MY
BREAKS ON SOME OF■@■@■@ROUTES.
THAT POINT AND WORKING ON?
>> RECEIVER DRILLS LIKE WHEN I
CUT AND EXPLODE INSTEAD OF COAST
OUT.
>> LET'S FOCUS@g WHATO
REALLY WELL, HIGH LEVEL, WATCH
THIS PLAY HERE.
THIS IS THE ONE SINGLE PLAY I'VE
WATCHED ALL YEAR LONG.
TAKE US THROUGH WHAT YOU'RE
THINKING HERE?
>> I KNEW HE WAS GOING TO TRY TO
JAM ME WITH THE INSIDE ARM.
AFS WAITING FOR THE JAM.
WHEN HE THREW IT USED MY
PHYSICALITY AND KNOCKED HIS ARM
DOWN AND BEAT HIM WITH MY FEET.
>> PERFECT.
MPRESSED.
>> ABIT, YEAH.
>> LIKE EIGHT, NINE YARDS OF
SEPARATION.
>> SINCE I HAVE YOU HERE AND YOU
DO STUDY SO MUCH FILM AND
LOOKING AT SO MANY TOP
RECEIVERS, WHAT'S THE PART OF
HIS GAME THAT IS STANDING OUT
THAT YOU KNOW THAT THE TEAMS ARE
GOING, THIS IS OUR GUY.
>> 6'3", 228, LOW 4.3s.
WE CAN WORK WITH IT.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S WHERE YOU HAVE TO
DOMINATE.
THE RED ZONE.
TOUCHDOWN, FIELD GOAL, BIG
DIFFERENCE WHO WINS FOOTBALL
GAMES.
YOU HAVE TO BE THE GUY THE
QUARTERBACK KNOWS AND
COORDINATOR GOES I HAVE A
NIGHTMARE MATCHUP FOR THE CORNER
AND BEAT THAT GUY LIKE A DRUM
AND GET THE TOUCHDOWN.
>> KEEP WORKING GETTING OFF THE
PRESS.
THAT WAS AWESOME THERE.
SO MANY DIFFERENT THINGS YOU
WILL HAVE TO LEARN.
YOU WILL LEARN OVER TIME.
GETTING OFF THE PRESS IS GOING
TO BE HUGE FOR YOU.
ONCE YOU GET GOING THAT SPEED ■
>> SPEAKING OF WHICH, COME ON,
WITH WE'RE GOING, NEXT STATION.
SO WE KNOW THAT YOU FAC LOT
OF GREAT DEFENDERS, SEC, BEST■
CONFERENCE IN COLLEGE FOOTBALL.
DIFFERENT IN THE NF
>>GHT, RYAN■XRK?■■J SO --
CAN EXPLAIN TO ■8■÷■8■8■8
HE NEED TO BE READY FOR WHEN
YOU'RE FACING GUYSTHE ■@■p■
■p THING LIKE YOU ■á■■■ AND■>
HAD THAT PLAY AGAINST SAVION. T
THDB POSITION.
ONE THING THEY WILL TRY TO DO
CAUSE YOU'RE S■@■@ YOU
T■ NG TO SHADE
YOU TO THE OUTSIDE.
SAVION WAS DOING■2■2■2■2 HE'S G
TO SHADE YOU TO THE OUTSIDE.
HE WANTS TO MAKE THE OUTSIDE
RELEASE DIFFICULT FOR YOU.
IF I MISS OUT HERE IT'S -- IF A
GUY IS SHADING YOU HERE AND YOU
HAVE A MANDATORY OUTSIDE RELEASE
AT
TO YOUR LANDMARK.
>> SQUARE HIM UP.
>> I GOT YOU.
>> HEAD UP NOW.
>> SQUARE HIM UP, GET MY ONE-TWO
OR A SPEED RELEASE AND USE MY
ARMS.
>> SO I TRAINED WHITE AND
JACKSON.
THESE ARE SMALLER GUYS YOU KNOW
FROM LSU PLAYING IN THOSE TIMES.
I WOULD TELL THEM TO SOFT SHOE
YOU A LITTLE BIT.
YOU DON'T WANT THOSE GUYS HAND
FIGHTING WITH YOU.
IF THEY GIVE YOU A LITTLE SPACE
HERE TO CREATE SPACE AND TRY TO
MAKE YOU GET OFF THE RELEASE ANO
BE YOUR MOVE THEN?
YOU TALK ABOUT GETTING IN AND
OUT OF CUTS.
THAT'S GOING TO BE A TIME WHERE
YOU HAVE TO MAKE QUICK MOVEMENT
LATERALLY.
IF HE SOFT SHOES OFF YOU, WHAT'S
EXT MOVE FOR HI
>>RYc■O GET HERE, RIGHT.
>> CUSHION RIGHT THERE.
>> HE SHOOTS THIS HAND.
>> I'M GOING TO --
>> GO HERE.
I GOT YOU.
THE FINAL THING FOR YOU WOULD BE
OBVIOUSLY FINISHING ON THE BALL.
I SEE THINGS/> AND TODD
HAVE DONE.
I SAW A PLAY AGAINST McFADDEN
WHERE YOU HIGH POINT THE BALL.
OBVIOUSLY THESE GUYS WILL TRY TO
PLAY THROUGH YOUR HANDS AND BODY
YOU.
WHAT DO YOU DO TO SEPARATE AT
THE BREAK-POINT TO MAKE SURE YOU
HAVE ENOUGH SPACE TO CREATE A
GOOD THROW FOR YOUR QUARTERBACK?
>> CHICKEN WING.
>> WHAT'S A CHICKEN WING?
THAT'S NOT A DEF TERM.
TELL ME WHAT A CHICKEN WING IS.
>> WHEN THEY GET CLOSE TO ME AND
THE BALL IS COMING, LAST --
>> GOING TO CHEAT?
>> THAT'S NOT CHEATING.
>> I NEVER GOT CALLED FOR IT.
NOT CHEATING.
>> IT'S ONLY CHEATING IF YOU GET
CAUGHT.
YOU KNOW, I NEVERHOUGHT I
WOULD LIKE A GUY FROM OLE MISS
YALL RIGHT.
I LIKE TA
CHICKEN WING.
>>> ALL RIGHT.VE NO TECHNIQUE F
ANY COACHING TIPS, BUT I
SOMETHING ABOUT GETTING INSIDE
INFORMATION AND THIS GUY THAT
YOU'RE ABOUT TO MEET, ADAM
GF IT,
PROBABLY BLOW YOUR PHONE UP ALL
SEASON LONG ASKING FOR
INFORMATION.
HE'S THE BEST AT WHAT HE DOES
AND BEST AT KNOWING WHAT TEAMS
ARE THINKING AND DOING.
THE PULSE ON HIS VALUE RIGHT
NOW, WHERE YOU THINK HE FALLS,
WHAT CAN YOU SHARE?
>> LOOK, THERE ARE SO MANY
PLACES THAT CAN USE A GUY LIKE
D.K. METCALF.
THE QUESTION IS WHERE HE GOES IN
THE FIRST ROUND, IF HE MAKES IT
INTO THE FIRST ROUND.
HE'S A FIRST ROUND TALENT.
LOOK ACROSS THE BOARD, SO MANY
TEAMS THAT NEED WIDE RECEIVER
HELP.
WOULDN'T PITTSBURGH MAKE SENSE.
IMAGINE KANSAS CITY.
IF THE CHIEFS WERE TO TAKE A GUY
LIKE D.K. METCALF AND PUT HIM
WITH PATRICK MAHOMES.
ALSO THE CHANCE THAT MAYBE YOU
SLIDE OUT OF THE FIRST ROUND, ■H
TO FIGURE OUT DON'T MAKE IT IN
THE FIRST ROUND, GO TO THE
SECOND ROUND, A SHORTER
CONTRACT, MAKE ALL THE TEAMS
THAT PASSED ON YOU PAY FOR
PASSING ON YOU.
LOOK, THERE ARE SO MANY WIDE
RECEIVER NEEDING TEAMS, HE'S ONE
OF THE TOP IF NOT THE TOP WIDE
RECEIVER ON THE BOARD, WE'LL SEE
TDE TO DO WITH IT.
>> WE KNOW MOST RECEIVERS
ENTERING ARE WILLING TO PLAY
WITH ANY QUARTERBACK, ANYONE
THAT CAN THEM THE BALL.
IN TERMS OF A SYSTEM FROM WHAT
YOU KNOW FROM WATCHING, IS THERE
A SYSTEM THAT YOU SEE UP HERE IN
YOU KNOW, THAT WOULD BE -- THAT
WOULD FIT ME REAL WELL?
>> ADD■ MORE TEAMS THAN YEAH.
I SEE THEM ALL.
>> THAT IS A■#■#■# GOOD ANSWER.
ALL RIGHT.
GUYS, STILL TO COME ON■ "NFL
LIVE," YOU DID PRETTY GOOD, BY .
PASSED THE GMS HERE LIKE
YOU.
LOUIS RIDDICK GOING TO BREAK
DOWN HIS FAVORITE PLAYERS IN THE
DRAFT AND WHY THEY WILL EXCEL NO
MATTER WHAT. , , ,
With Graer,
you'll dare to put a twist on
the traditional
that will lead you to somewhere
unexpected.
Somewhere you can create
something...
better than good.
Here, you'll create something
grand.
Grand Marnier.
A visionary blend of fine cognac
and bitter orange liqueur.
Live Grand.
Rated M for mature.
One bullet left...
...who's it for?
The strong?
The weak?
Or the hopeless?
This world will come for
you, and it will never stop.
One bullet left...
...who's it for?
Reese's eggs are back
and we hid them
somewhere you'll never find...
Sike! We put them everywhere.
and chiropractor's,
bowling alleys,
which we already mentioned...
and chiropractor's,
bowling alleys,
WENDY'S BIGGIE BAG, HUH.
IT'S EVERYTHING YOU EVER
WANTED FOR JUST 5 BUCKS.
EVERYTHING I EVER WANTED?
THAT'S RIGHT.
A BACON DOUBLE STACK WITH A
QUARTER POUND OF FRESH BEEF,
NUGGETS, FRIES AND A
DRINK FOR JUST 5 BUCKS.
WENDY'S BIGGIE BAG IS
EVERYTHING YOU EVER WANTED.
IF YOU HAVE A GARDEN YOU KNOW,
WEEDS ARE LOWDOWN
LITTLE SCOUNDRELS.
DRAW THE LINE WITH ROUNDUP.
THE SURE SHOT WAND EXTENDS
WITH A PROTECTIVE SHIELD
TO TARGET WEEDS PRECISELY
AND KILL THEM RIGHT
DOWN TO THE ROOT.
ROUNDUP BRAND.
TRUSTED FOR OVER 40 YEARS.
>>> PERFECT TIMING, ESPN'S DRAFT
ACADEMY IS BACK.
EIGHT EPISODES, DOCUMENTARY,
IT'S GOING TO TAKE A LITTLE BIT
BEHIND THE SCENES, GETS VERY
PERSONAL, INTO THE LIVES OF
PROJECTED FIRST ROUND PICKS LIKE
NICK BOSA AND DREW LOCK.
THE FIRST ON ESPN PLUS AND TREND
ON THE ESPN APP.
START YOUR FREE STYLE TODAY.
SOME OF THE BEST STUFF WE DO
HERE.
>> FAVORITE SHOW.
>> IT'S GREAT.
GETS YOU READY AND PUMPED AND
KIND OF --
>> NOT JUST BECAUSE KIPER'S ON
IT.
>> WE'VE SEEN ENOUGH KIPER THE
LAST FEW WEEKS.
THAT SAID, LOUIS, YOU HAVE SOME
FAVORITES IN THIS DRAFT CLASS
COMING UP HERE.
>> YEAH.
>> AND WE'RE CURIOUS WHAT YOUR
PROJECTED TOP FIVE FAVORITE GUYS
ARE.W DOME UP WITH THIS
LIST OF W THEY'RE TOP
FIVE FAVORITE.
>> NOT THE TOP FIVE THAT I THINK
WILL GO OFF THE BOARD.
MY TOP FIVE FAVORITE GUYS IN
TERMS OF SCHEME, VERSATILITY,
HOW THEY PLAY THE GAME AND
VE BEEN.
WHEN PRODUCTIVE AT THE COLLEGE
LEVEL AND HIGH-LEVEL
COMPETITION, YOU'LL BE
PRODUCTIVE IN THE PROS.
NUMBER FIVE EXEMPLIFIES JUST
THAT.
■■■k■y■y■■■y■÷ú, MICHIGAN IS ONF
THE GUYS WHEN YOU LOOK AT HIM
COMPARED TO SOME OF THE OTHER
HIGH-PROFILE PLAYERS IN THE
DRAFT, YOU'RE GOING HE'S NOT■■■
THEIR CLASS.
HE LINES UP OPPOSITE A GUY ON
HIS OWN FOOTBALL TEAM NAMED
RASHAN GARY, HE'S TWICE THE
PLAYER PLAYS WITH A BETTER
MOTOR, BETTE TECHNIQUE AND
AWAREN?h AND■7 HE HAS SCHEMED
DIVERSE.
HE CAN PLAY IN A THREE FOUR OR
FOUR THREE.
HE IS A GUY THAT CAN RUSH OVER A
GUARD IF YOU NEED HIM TO AND CAN
BEAT OFFENSIVE GUARDS.
I THINK IN THE PROS HIS GAME
WILL TRANSLATE DESPITE HE'S NOT
ONE OF THE HIGHLY TALKED ABOUT
PLAYERS IN THE DRAFT.
NUMBER FOUR,K ABOUT JOSH
JACOBS HERE WHO IS ONE OF MY
FAVORITE PLAYERS IN THE DRAFT
BECAUSE AS A RUNNING BACK HE CAN
RUN IN A Z SCHEME, IN A POWER
SCHEME.
HE CAN PASS PROTECT AND CATCH
THE BALL OUT OF THE BACKFIELD
AND BREAK THE HOME RUNS AND
FIRST AND FOREMOST HE WILL
ABSOLUTELY PUNISH YOU AND KNOCK
YOUR TEETH OUT.
THIS GUY ISo■■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ Ñ■
SO IN THE NFL, I T■ GAME )■TRANO
GUYS AGREE?
>> I DO.
I'LL TELL YOU, HOW ABOUT THE
PATRIOTS AND ROB NINKOVICH,
REMEMBER HIM, COMING UP.
>> BETTER ATHLETE THAN PEOPLE
THINK.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AND I DON'T MEAN TO SAY THAT
LIKE THIS IS A GUY THAT'S AN
OVERACHIEVER.
HE'S NOT.
THE STEREOTYPE PEOPLE TRY TO
ASSOCIATE WITH CHASE.
THIS GUY IS JUST A FANTASTIC
FOOTBALL PLAYER OVERALL.
NUMBER THREE, IT'S KIND OF
INTERESTING HERE, WHERE ARE YOU,
BUDDY.
NICK, THERE YOU GO.
LOOK, MOST PEOPLE WOULD SAY, NO
KIDDING, THIS GUY IS A GOOD
FOOTBALL PLAYER, PROBABLY GOING
NUMBER ONE OR TWO OVERALL.
THERE'S A REASON WHY I P■IM
ON HERE NOT JUST BECAUSE OF
WHERE PEOPLE PROJECT HIM.
JUST BECAUSE OF HOW HE PLAYS THE
GAME.
AND HOW SCHEME DIVERSE HE IS AND
o■ READY HE IS.■>
HE CAN PLAY THE RUN.
HE'S DISTINCTIVE AND NEEDS TO
STAY HEALTHY AND PLAY IN A THREE
FOUR OR FOUR THREE.
WHAT DO YOU NEED TO SAY AS FAR
AS HIS PROJECTION IS CONCERNED.
NOT MUCH ELSE TO TALK ABOUT WITH
A GUY LIKE NICK BOSA.
>> NUMBER TWO.
THIS IS ONE OF MY FAVORITE
PLAYERS IN THE DRAFT, IT'S NOT
YOU, KYLER, IT Iñ>■■■■Ñ■■■■■Ñ■Ñ
WILKINS WHO ON CLEMSON'S DEFENSE
I THINK HE IS THE GUY WHO STANDS
OUT AS THE GUY WHO IS MOST
CONSISTENT, AGAIN, A GUY WHO CAN
PLAY THE RUN, THE PASS, PLAY THE
ONE TECHNIQUE, THREETECHNIQUE,
CHASES THEOOTBALL.
YOU SEE 42 FLASHING ACROSS YOUR
SCREEN EVERY SINGLE DEFENSIVE ■
YOU LOOK AT HOW --
>> SPECIAL TEAMS AND SOMETIMES
THE GOAL LINE.
>> HEY, EXACTLY.
AS GOOD AS THIS KID HAS BEEN IN
THE PROS, HIS GAME IS THE KIND
OF GAME THAT TRANSFERS TO THE
PRO GAME.
AND THEN NUMBER ONE, LOOK --
>> DYING TO SEE THIS.
>> I AM JUST ENAMORED WITH DEVIN
I PLAYED WITH HIS FATHER IN
ATLANTA, DEVIN BUSH A SAFETY
FROM@■■ FLORIDA STATE.
THIS KID IS TWICE THE ATHLETE
HIS DAD WAS AND HIS DAD WAS HELL
ON WHEELS AS FAR AS
HITT
■ O■  THE SPOT AS FAR ■>■■8■>■>
BUCKLING THE HEADS OF OFFENSIVE
LINEMEN THE WAY HE TAKES THEM
ON.
FAST AS YOU KNOW WHAT.
HE CAN GET TO THE PERIMETER AND
MAKE IMPACT PLAYS AGAINST THE
RUN AND COVER.
>> I LOVE DEVIN FROM LSU.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S A
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN WHITE AND
BUSH.
>> I'M TAKING THIS KID WITHIN
THE TOP TEN BECAUSE OF THE WAY
TEAMS PLAY OFFENSE RIGHT NOW,
YOU BETTER■J■R■RUYS LIKE THIS
HE'S GOING TO BE AN ALL PRO
QUICKLY.
>> FEW WEEKS AGO THAT DWAYNE
HASKINS HAD HIS PRO DAY
CALLED LOU THAT NIGHT, HOW GOOD
IS HE?
>> YOU DON'T KNOW HOW GOOD THIS
GUY IS.
HE'S SO GOOD.
YOU DON'T HAVE HIM IN YOUR TOP
FIVE OR A QUARTERBACK.
>> I'LL TELL YOU THIS, LOOK, I
LOVE DWYANE HASKINS I'M ALL-IN
AND I COULD HAVE PUT HIM ON THIS
LIST.
ALTHOUGH I WILL SAY THIS, THIS
LIST RIGHT HERE, I THINK THESE
GUYS EVEN THOUGH THEY'RE NOT
WHAT I WOULD REALLY TERM AS
TRANSCENDENT PLAYERS, I THINK
THEY ARE TAYLOR MADE FOR THE
NFL.
DWYANE'S FUTURE SUCCESS WILL BE
PENDENT ON WHERE HE'S DRAFTING
AND COACHING HIM.
ALTHOUGH I'M NOT DOWN ON HIM AT
ALL.
CODY FORD IS ANOTHER ONE MY
FAVORITE PLAYERS IN THE DRAFT.
>> THE GUY FROM OKLAHOMA.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> NOT A RIGHT TACKLE HE'S GOING
TO BE A DARN GOOD OFFEN
>> PRO BOWL OFFENSIVE LINE.
>> AND MARQUESS --
>> AS LONG AS HE STAYS HEALTHY.
>> 166 POUNDS, I GOT IT.
TODAY'S NFL SPACE CREATING
PLAYS.
>> YEAH.
>> VERTICALS, ASPECT, BEING ABLE
TO DRIVE DEFENSES OFF.
HE DOES EVERYTHING YOU LOOK FOR.
>> ALL THESE GUYS.
>> PRODUCTION.
AND VERSATILITY.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> WHAT DID WE SAY ABOUT
CHRISTIAN, HE'S A MAN.
ALL■■■■ WILL COME INTO
THE NFL AND HAVE THE IMMEDIATE
IMPACT AND I THINK WIN KNOW
VICH, SECOND ROUND PICK, DOESN'T
MEAN -- HAS A CHAPS TO BE A HECK
OF A PLAYER.
DEVIN BUSH, I THINK RIGHT NOW, I
WOULD MAKE A STRONG ARGUMENT
HE'S A SIXTH OR SEVENTH BEST
PLAYER IN THIS DRAFT AND COULD
GO TOP TEN AFTER ALL IS SAID AND
DONE.
FOUR FIRSTS ON THIS LIST AND
ONLY SECOND ROUND PICK I THINK
MAYBE THIRD ROUND, SHOT TO DROP
INTO THE THIRD, BUT WIN KNOW
VICH, THAT NINKOVICH PRODUCTION.
>> OVER RASHAN GARY IN THE
YOU LIKE NICK BOSA'S
TECHNIQUE AND HAND USE YOU WILL
LOVE HIS TECHNIQUE AND HIS
HAPPENED USE.
B■■ THE SIZE OF■ E
MAYBE DOESN'T HAVE THE PHYSICAL
UPSIDE OF HIM --
>> WHY IS -- ■>> HE
IS HIS TECHNIQUE AND HAND
USE SO GOOD AND THE OTHER GUY
WHO HAS THE SAME COACH --
>> RASHAN GARY.
>> NEVER FIGURED IT OUT.
THAT'S WHAT'S CONCERNING TO ME.
>> VON MILLER I BELIEVE I READ
WHERE HE SAID GUYS WHO RUSH THE
PASSER AND PLAY GOOD IN THE
COLLEGE FOOTBALL AGAINST GOOD
COMPETITION GENERALLY ARE GOOD
PLAYERS IN THE PROS.
THESE GUYS ALL OF THEM ARE GOOD
PLAYERS AGAINST GREAT
COMPETITION.
THEY'RE GOING TO BE GREAT PROS.
>> A LOT OF GUYS THESE GUYS ARE
GOING UP AGAINST WILL HAVE
ANOTHERUPATION.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> THE GUYS IN THE NFL ARE THE
BEST IN THE WORLD.
YOU CAN'T GO AGAINST GUYS
PLAYING AND DOING SOMETHING
ELSE.
>> YEAH.
>> ONCE THEIR COLLEGE CAREER IS
OVER HOW WILL YOU DO IT AGAINST
THE BEST IN THE WORLD.
>> YOU PEOPLE AT HOME TWEET
SAYING ALL WE DO IS TALK ABOUT
QUARTERBACKS.
WE MENTIONED ONE.
>> YOU MADE ME TALK ABOUT IT.
■÷ TOP F■O■O■ ■■■■I■/■■■(]■v■L■;
■/■/■/■
UNTHINKABLE HAPPENED.
KA TRADED ALL OF THE
PICKS TO GET RICKY WILLIAMS IN
THE '99 DRAFT.
A LOOK BACK AT THAT CRAZY TRADE
AND WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT NEXT.
b■
IF YOU HAVE A GARDEN YOU KNOW,
WEEDS ARE LOWDOWN
LITTLE SCOUNDRELS.
DRAW THE LINE WITH ROUNDUP.
THE SURE SHOT WAND EXTENDS
WITH A PROTECTIVE SHIELD
TO TARGET WEEDS PRECISELY
AND KILL THEM RIGHT
DOWN TO THE ROOT.
ROUNDUP BRAND.
TRUSTED FOR OVER 40 YEARS.
With Instant Confirmation...
I got it!
What?
L.A.
Bookers book apartments
and vacation homes
as easy as hotels.
Ridin' scooter!
L.A. Baby!
Be a Booker
You're welcome.
at Booking.com
There are those who see the
challenges facing
the nation and say send me.
They fight for country.
They fight for honor.
They fight to win.
DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES?■
Find out at goarmy.com/warriors
>>> TONIGHT DON'T FORGET TO
WATCH SPORTS CENTER AT 6:00
EASTERN.
WE'RE GOING TO BE TALKING ABOUT
WARRIORS AS THEY RESPOND TO
PATRICK BEVERLY'S BATTLE WITH
K.D. AND RED SOX AND YANKEES ON
ESPN.
WHICH TEAM FEELING THE PRESSURE.
AND RUSSELL WILSON, TALK ABOUT
THAT RECORD-BREAKING NFL DEAL.
HE SPOKE WITH THE MEDIA TODAY.
WE WILL HAVE ALL OF THAT COMING
UP AT 6:00.
DON'T FORGET IF YOU'RE NOT IN
FRONT OF THE TELEVISION YOU HAVE
IT ON THE APP.
>>> THERE HAS BEEN A TRADE
INVOLVING THIS FIFTH PICK IN THE
DRAFT.
THEY NOW GET ONE, THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN AND A ONE AND A
THREE NEXT YEAR.
THE NEW OS■
RICKY WILLIAMS, RUNNING BACK,
UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS.
>> YOU HAVE NO MORE PICKS NOW.
WHAT WILL YOU DO WITH THE REST
OF THE DAY?
>> GONE GOLFING.
DON'T YOU THINK?
>> SHADY AND■÷÷÷
????■k?kP■■/
SNOWE.
>> RICKY!
>> WE TOOK OR EGGS AND THREW
THEM IN THE ONE BASKET AND WE'RE
SATISFIED WITH DOING THAT.
>> 20 YEARS AGO, GUYS, MIKE
DITKA THEY TRADE AWAY EIGHT
DRAFT PICKS TO MOVE UP TO FIFTH
OVERALL TO TAKE RUNNING BACK
RICKY WILLIAMS.
LOOK AT ALL THOSE PICKS.
WILLIAMS ENTERED AFTER RUSHING
OVER 2,000 YARDS AND WON THE '98
HEISMAN TROPHY AT THE UNIVERSITY
OF TEXAS.
GUYS, HOW ABOUT PROBABLY THE
BEST COVER IN ESPN MAGAZINE
HISTORY, ONE OF THE TOP ONES.
DITKA, WILLIAMS, ON THE COVER.
THE PICTURE WORTH A THOUSAND
WORDS.
I WAS DOING RESEARCH ON IT,
WILLIAMS ACTUALLY IS THE ONE WHO
CAME UP WITH THE IDEA TO WEAR
THE WEDDING DRESS.
IT WASN'T OUR COMPANY.
HE THOUGHT IT WOULD BE FITTING
BECAUSE IT WAS A MARRIAGE■  THA
ENDED --
>> QUICKLY.
>> ENDED --
>> SO SCHEFTER, I KNOW YOU WERE
OUT IN DENVER AT THE TIME
COVERING THE BRONCOS WHEN THIS
WENT DOWN.
A YOUNG BUCK.
WHAT DO YOU REMEMBER?
>> THERE ARE A FEW THINGS THAT
STAND OUT.
I REMEMBER IN A DRAFT BEFORE
THEN, DAN REEVES SAYING HE WOULD
BE WILLING TO TRADE HIS ENTIRE
DRAFT FOR STEVE COMING OUT OF
THE UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON AT
THAT TIME.
EVERY NOW AND THEN YOU GET A
PLAYER LIKE RICKY WHO A TEAM IS
GOING TO TRADE ALL THE PICKS
FOR.
THIS TRADE, THE SAINTS■ttq4■ññ■.
THE REDSKINS PARLAYED THAT INTO
CHAMP BAILEY AMONGST OTHER
PLAYERS BUT THE REDSKINS SHOULD
HAVE BEEN SET UP TO WIN SUPER
BOWLS FOR PICKS LIKE THAT.
THERE ARE TEAMS TODAY THAT WOULD
KILL TO HAVE A BOUNTY OF PICKS
LIKE THAT.
THE ONLY WAY TEAMS TODAY, THE
ONLY WAY AODAY WOULD
TRADE ALL THOSE PICKS IN MY MIND
WOULD BE FOR A QUARTERBACK.
THAT'S IT.
BUT BACK THEN, IT WAS A HUGE
TRADE AND I MEAN■8 STILL
REMEMBER THAT.
BIG ONES LIKE THAT.
ABOUT AS BIG A TRADE OTHER THAN
THE HERSCHEL WALKER TRADE WE'VE
SEEN.
>> I WAS A 19-YEAR-OLD COLLEGE
STUDENT AT THE TIME IN LOUISIANA
AND IT WAS JUST NUTS.
IT WAS CRAZY BECAUSE YOU HAD
SPECTRUM, PEOPLE WHO WERE SUPER
EXCITED THAT WE HAD GOT RICKY
WILLIAMS, A HEISMAN TROPHY
WINNER, AND PEOPLE ON THE OTHER
SIDE, ONE, THINKINGD■■
Y STUPID AND TWO THE■■
THAT ENSUED AFTERWARDS,
MIKE DITKA COMING IN WITH■qr
■=■= ESPN ■/jCOVER.
IT BECAME SOMETHING THAT WAS
EMBARRASS PG.
IT WAS A FIASCO.
FOR PEOPLE WHO WERE A PART OF IT
OR CLOSE TO IT, YOU KNOW, LIKE I
WAS BEING IN THAT STATE, IT WAS
A VERY, VERY WEIRD TIME TO
FIGURE OUT HOW PEOPLE FELT ABOUT
THE DECISION THAT MIKE DITKA AND
THE SAINTS MADE TO GET RICKY
WILLIAMS.
>> MY CAREER WAS JUST ENDING AT
THAT TIME ON MY WAY OUT OF THE
NFL AND I REMEMBER JUST LOOKING
AT THE DRAFT AND SITTING THERE
THINKING YOU GAVE UP YOUR ENTIRE
DRAFT FOR ONE PLAYER?
THAT WOULD NEVER HAPPEN IN
TODAY'S GAME.
I DON'T CARE IF IT WAS A
QUARTERBACK OR NOT, NOT WITH THE
WAY GENERAL MANAGERS VALUE PICKS
AND DRAFT CURRENCY.
ALL THOSE PICKS.
IT WAS -- NO ONE WOULD DO THAT
NOW.
>> THE LAST TIME I SAW THAT MANY
WAS RG3.
>> I HAVE A QUESTION.
DO YOU THINK A TEAM WOULD GIVE
UP ITS WHOLE DRAFT SAY AARON
RODGERS IN HIS PRIME?
IF YOU WERE WILLING TO TRADE
HIM --
>> IF YOU KNEW --
>> IN HIS PRIME.
>> TALKING ABOUT --
>> YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT --
>> AARON FOUR YEARS AGO.
>> A VETERAN QUARTERBACK --
>> WITH THEY DO SOMETHING
LIKE --
>> AARON FOUR YEARS AGO --
>> I DON'T KNOW MAN.
>> IT'S HARD.
>> THAT'S A LOT.
I MEAN YOUR ENTIRE DRAFT
PLUS PICKS IN THE FOLLOWING
DRAFT.
THAT'S A LOT.
>> THAT'S HOW --
>> THAT'S HOW CRAZY IT IS.
PEOPLE WOULDN'T DO THAT FOR
PRIME AARON RODGERS, AND THE
SAINTS DID THAT FOR RICKY
WILLIAMS.
>> EXACTLY.
>> THAT'S HOW CRAZY THAT IS.
>> IT IS.
>> I WAS THINKING BACK TO LAST
YEAR WE ALL WOULD AGREE THAT
SAQUON WAS ABOUT AS HIGH A RATED
RUNNING BACK.
WOULD ANY TEAM EVER --
>> NO.
>> NO WAY.
>> NO CHANCE.
>> NOT THAT POSITION.
>> MOST JUST MOVE UP AND GET
HIM.
>> NOT FOR THAT POSITION IN
PARTICULAR.
>> ARGUING THE GIANTS SHOULDN'T
HAVE DRAFTED HIM --
>> THIS TRADE EVEN --
>> THAT'S --
>> IT'S BIZARRE.
>> WE CAN ALL AGREE THERE IS NOT
A PLAYER IN THIS DRAFT RIGHT
NOW.
>> NO.
>> THAT WOULD BE -- ALL RIGHT.
HOW ABOUT WOULD THERE BE A
PLAYER WHO --
>> ACTUALLY --
>> IF I COULD GET ADAM SCHEFTER
I WOULD DO IT.
>> I THINK SOMEBODY WOULD BE
WILLING TO GIVE THAT UP FOR --
>> WHO.
>> TREVOR WILLIAMS.
THE CLEMSON QUARTERBACK.
TREVOR LAWRENCE.
>> AN ENTIRE DRAFT PLUS
TWO PICKS IN THE FOLLOWING
DRAFT.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
PREDICTING.
>> TREVOR LAWRENCE.
SOMEBODY WOULD BE WILLING TO
GIVE THAT FOR TREVOR LAWRENCE.
>> I'M GLAD YOU CORRECTED IT.
WHY DON'T I KNOW THAT
QUARTERBACK.
OH, MY GOSH.
I HAVE TO STUDY.
>> NEVER HEARD OF TREVOR
WILLIAMS.
THAT'S THE NEW GUY.
UP AND COMING.
TREVOR LAWRENCE.
>> BEFORE WE WRAP UP THIS
EDITION OF "NFL LIVE" AND GET
THE NAMES STRAIGHT, WE'RE GOING
TO TELL YOU WHAT GAMES WE'RE
LOOKING FORWARD TO.
THE NFL SCHEDULE RELEASE TONIGHT
AT 8:00.
FIVE...
FOUR...
THREE...
TWO...
ONE...
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU LIVED ON THE EDGE?
CASTROL EDGE
LIVE ON THE EDGE
IT'S MORE THAN JUST OIL.
IT'S LIQUID ENGINEERING.
♪♪
Staying at Hampton
for a work trip.
When your
flight gets in late,
it's never too
early for coffee.
Oh no no no.
Your new boss
seems cool,
but she might not
be sweatpants cool.
Who is THAT
ready THIS early?
It's only 7 am.
Somebody help me.
Close call.
Not quite ready
to face the day?
That's why we're here
with free hot breakfast
and a warm welcome.
Book at Hampton.com for
our Price Match Guarantee.
Hampton by Hilton.
Each day Justin
chooses to walk.
Book at Hampton.com for
our Price Match Guarantee.
At w■■7■97♪xxxxx;
ó>ó>And after ó>■■?■■■çá
Each day Justin
chooses to walk.
He does it all with
Dr. Scholl's.
Only Dr. Scholl's has
Massaging Gel Insoles
that provide
all-day comfort.
To keep him feeling
more energized.
Dr. Scholl'@ to Move.■
Reese's eggs are back
and we hid them
somewhere you'll never find...
Sike! We put them everywhere.
Grocery stores and
supermarkets, gas stations,
which we already mentioned...
g
Grocery stores and
supermarkets, gas stations,
I have discovered something
called a "preservative"!
We could put it in Bud Light
and make it last forever!
Why would I want it to last
forever
if I'm going to drink it now.
You could drink it now.
But Light. No corn syrup, no
preservatives,
and no artificial flavors.
Experience the style,
craftsmanship and technology
that have made the RX
the leading luxury
SUV of all time.
Lease the 2019 RX 350 for
$409 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
>>> COMING UP, THE RELEASE OF
THE ENTIRE SCHEDULE FOR THE 2019
SEASON, ALL THE RIVALRY AND
PRIME TIME GAMES, AND ALL THE
PLAYOFF REMATCHES, EVERY TEAM'S
SCHEDULE FROM WEEK ONE TO■
WILL BE REVEALED.
IT'S A SPORTS CENTER SPECIAL ON
ESPN AND ESPN 2 AND■íg■■>■í■>■■
>>> WE HEARD WENDI NIX'S VOICE
BECAUSE SHE IS GOING TO BE
ANCHORING TONIGHT ON ESPN 2 AT
8:00 WHEN THE SCHEDULES ARE
FINALLY REVEALED.
ONE OF THE MOST EXCITING THINGS
THAT HAPPENS IN THE OFFSEASON.
SO THAT SAID IN TERMS OF THE
REMATCHES, WE HAVE LOTS OF
FORMER PLAYERS GOING UP
AGAINST -- A LOT OF PLAYERS
GOING UP AGAINST THEIR FORMER
TEAMS, IS THERE A MATCHUP THAT
YOU WANT TO SEE THAT YOU'RE MOST
LOOKING FORWARD TO?
RYAN, I WOULD LIKE TO START WITH
YOU ON THAT?
>> THIS IS A NO-BRAINER.
I WANT TO SEE Le'VEON GET AN
OPPORTUNITY TO PLAY AGAINST THE
PITTSBURGH STEELERS.
HE SAT OUT ALL YEAR, WANTED TO
GET HIS BIG DEAL, GOT THE MONEY
HE WANTED AND YOU GET TO GO BACK
AND PLAY YOUR FORMER TEAM.
THAT'S THINGS YOU DREAM ABOUT.
HE WILL WANT TO SHOW THEM UP AND
THEY MISSED OUT ON HAVING THEM
AS THEIR RUNNING BACK AND YOU
KNOW THE PITTSBURGH STEELERS,
ARE GOING TO WANT TO PROVE TO
THEM THAT WE ARE ALL RIGHT
WITHOUT YOU.
IT'S LIKE WHEN YOUR GIRL LEAVES
YOU FOR SOMEBODY ELSE YOU WANT
TO SHOW HER I HAVE A FRESH
HAIRCUT AND NICE SUIT AND DOING
GOOD TOO.
>> IT'S CALLED THE REVENGE GAME.
>> YEAH.
>> LY.
>> START GOING TO THE GYM A
LITTLE MORE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> WEARING BETTER CLOTHES.
>> RIGHT.
>> A FRESH CUT.
YOU KNOW IT, YOU GOT TO.
>> YEAH.
>> I LOVE IT.
>> I LOVE THAT.
>> WHAT A PROCESS.
ALWAYS APPLIES TO FOOTBALL.
NEVER UNDERSTAND WHY.
>> I'M GOING CHIEFS/PATRIOTS.
THAT'S THE ONE I WANT TO SEE.
IT'S GOING TO BE CHIEFS AT
PATRIOTS AGAIN.
HOPEFULLY ONE OF THE GAMES LATE
IN THE SEASON WHERE THERE'S A
LOT ON THE LINE.
LOOK YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN ONE OFFSIDE
PENALTY, MAYBE BETWEEN ONE TEAM
BEING IN THE SUPER BOWL AND THE
OTHER.
>> YEP.
>> SCHEFFTY, WHAT DO YOU GOT?
>> A SENTENCE WE HAVEN'T HEARD
SINCE THE EARLY 1980s.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THE BROWNS
AND JETS WHO USED TO MEET IN THE
PLAYOFFS IN THE ■■■ AND HAVE EN
ARE NOW POISED TO HAVE ONE
OF THE MOST INTRIGUING MATCH-UPS
OF THE UPCOMING SEASON.
CLEVELAND IN NEW YORK.
ODELL BECKHAM, JR., BACK IN
METLIFE STADIUM.
THE JETS WITH THAT IMPROVED
ROSTER.
BAKER MAYFIELD.
>> SOLD IT.
>> I'M NOT INTO IT.
>> AT FIRST I WAS LIKE --
>> HE SOLD IT.
>> IF YOU'RE NOT INTO THAT