Can.
With just 1.7 Carbs and 62 Cals,
you CAN enjoy a Michelob weekda.
Do you want ready to wear
clothing without all the hassle?
You can, wit Dryer
sheets.
We dried one shirt without
Bounce,
and an identical shirt using
Bounce.
The Bounce shirt has fewer
wrinkles, less static,
and more softness and
freshness.
Bounce out wrinkles, Bounce out
static.
I can't tell you who I am
or what I witnessed,
but I can tell you Liberty
Mutual customized my
car insurance so I only
pay for what I need.
Oh no, no, no, no,
no, no, no...
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
my dream car.
It turns out, they want
me to start next month.
She can stay with you to
finish her senior year.
Things will be tight but,
we can ma♪ ♪this work.
Now...
Grandpa, what about
your dream car?
This is my dream now.
Principal we can help
you plan for that .
Butterfinger?
Better Butterfinger.
[echoing]
Better Butterfinger...
♪
An improved recipe with
high quabo peanuts
B■■■■■■■AA■■■■
that are crispety,
crunchety and peanut buttery.
♪
Each day Justin
chooses to walk.
At99■xx■9=-=■=■=i=■■
ó>And afte■■■
Each day Justin
chooses to walk.
He does it all with
Dr. Scholl's.
Only Dr. Scholl's has
Massaging Gel Insoles
that provide
all-day comfort.
To keep him feeling
more energized.
Dr. Scholl's.
o Move.■■)■ ■
Your eyes don't deceive you.
This taco is filled with
crunchy, melty nachos.
For just a dollar.
The new $1 Loaded
Nacho Taco from
Taco Bell's Cravings
Value Menu.
[BONG]
GREENY: "SPORTSCENTER" AT
6:00 EASTERN AFTER "P.T.I." WITH
KEVIN NEGANDHI AND KEITH
OLBERMANN.
HOW SOON THE LAKERS MAY MAKE
MAJOR MOVES AND HEAR FROM TIGERS
AT THE MASTERS AND REACTION TO
JAMEIS WINSTON PLANS TO PLAY
20-POUNDS HEAVIER THIS YEAR.
"SPORTSCENTER" AFTER "P.T.I." ON
ESPN■>■2■2PN APP.
A QUICK LOOK AT THIS.
ON PLANET EARTH, REMEMBER WHEN
ZION WILLIAMSON SHOWED UP AT THE
REC.
CENTER AFTER DUKE'S LOSS IN THE
TOURNAMENT AND DEMOLISHED A HOOP
AND A DUNK WITH A PICKUP GAME?
REMEMBER THIS, JALEN?
JALEN: I TRIED TO TELL YOU ALL.
GREENY: HE BASICALLY BROKE THE
BACKBOARD.
WE NOW KNOW THE FULL EXTENT OF
THE DAMAGE.
A TWEET FROM THE DUKE CHRONICLE.
POINTING IT OUT WITH THE CAPTION
TODAY AT THE BRODY RECREATION
CENTER IS CAUTION TAPE AND ZION
WAS HERE SIGN.
>> THERE WAS A LABEL THAT SAID
NO DUNKING ON THE RIM.
GREENY: HE GOT THE MONEY TO PAY
FOR IT.
ONE MORE FINAL THOUGHTS ON
VIRGINIA WINNING THE
CHAMPIONSHIP?
SEAN: THE BEST RECORD OVERALL IN
THE LAST TWO YEARS.
THEY GOT REDEMPTION.
THEY WIN THE TITLE.
GOOD FOR THEM AND TONY BENNETT.
JALEN: JOHN WOODEN SAID SPORTS
DOILD CHARACTER IT
REVEALS IT.
THEM TO COME BACK ANDTILL
MAINTAIN AS A NUMBER ONE SEED BY
ALL OF THE