ç8ç7ç7ç7ç7ç7ç7ç7ç7ç7ç7ç7ç7ç7ç7Ñj
that captured carbon like trees
we could help lower emissions.
Carbon Capture is important
technology -
and experts agree.
That's why we're working on ways
to improve it.
So plants...
can be a little more...
like plants.
♪ ♪
ing]
Theythe
[thinking]
Hot...hot...
♪Oohh, hot stuff
all over my nachos♪
ññóóó' like a taco♪
♪Driving over potholes♪
♪Hotter than a pot roast♪
♪Fingers on my hot chips♪
♪Red handed come on man♪
♪Now I'm a need some chopsticks♪
♪Speaking of desire babe♪
♪Preachin' to the choir♪
♪Man my tongue is doing fine♪
♪But the roof is on fire♪
♪Tell me why♪
♪I never wanna hear you say♪
The Original, now it's hot.
♪I want it ■■■>>>AAO■■
■;■;■■;■;■>ç■■2?;■
Run with us
in the unstoppable
John Deere Gator XUV835,
Because when others
take rain checks...
we take the wheel.
■g
Run with us.
Search "John Deere Gator"
for more.
■g
Run with us.
Everyone at school
has the glittery one.
Of course
she wants that one.
And she wants the
one with the doodads.
No one has the one
with doodads yet.
Because no one
can find it.
For the glittery one,
and the one with doodads.
eBay.
my dream car.
It turns out, they want
me to start next month.
She can stay with you to
finish her senior year.
Things will be tight but,
we can make this work. ♪
Now...
Grandpa, what about
your dream car?
This is my dream now.
Principal we can help
you plan for that .
♪  ♪
■■
Turn up your swagger
game with One A Day Gummies.
One serving...■
...once a day...
...and one healthy you.
That's The Power of One A Day.
Sometimes, all you have
to do is read the signs.
Miller Lite has more taste,
fewer calories, and half
the carbs of Bud Light.
What are you holding?
Miller Lite. Hold True.
ANNOUNCER: "SPORTSCENTER"
BROUGHT TO YOU BY THE UNEXPECTED
ENERGY OF EBIL.■
EBAY.
AND MICHELIN WIPER BLADES.
THEY'RE ALL THE DIFFERENCE, FOR
SAFER DRIVING ON THE ROAD.
>> BREAKING NEWS INTO
"SPORTSCENTER."
ANTONIO BROWN IS A RAIDER.
A NINE-YEAR CAREER IN PITTSBURGH
WAS PROLIFIC.
>> THE RAIDERS ARE THE TEAM THAT
MADE THE MOST SENSE.
IT'S GOING TO BE FOR A
THIRD-ROUND PICK.IT GOING TO BEH
ROUND PICK SO IT'S NOT EXACTLY A
HUGE RETURN FOR A PLAYER THAT
HAS HAD THE UNPARALLELED
PRODUCTION THAT ANTONIO BROWN
HAS HAD.
KEVIN: ANTONIO BROWN IS IN
OAKLAND NOW.
HE STILL HAS PITTSBURGH ON HIS
MIND.
YESTERDAY HE RESPONDED TO A
TWEET WHICH SHOWED JUJU
SMITH-SCHUSTER AS THE STEELERS
M.V.P.
SAYING "EMOTION.
BOY FUMBLED THE WHOLE POSTSEASON
IN THE BIGGEST GAME OF THE YEAR.
EVERYONE WENT BLIND.
NOT ENOUGH REALITY THESE DAYS."
JUJU RESPONDED SAYING "KEEP YOUR
EMOTIONS OFF THE INTERNET.
ALL I EVER DID WAS SHOW THAT MAN
LOVE AND RESPECT FROM THE MOMENT
HE GOT TO THE LEAGUE.
I WAS GENUINELY HAPPY FOR HIM,
TOO.
CRAZY HOW BIG THAT EGO GOT TO BE
TO TAKE SHOTS AT PEOPLE WHO SHOW
YOU LOVE, SHAKING MY HEAD."
THEN BROWN FIRING BACK,
PUBLICIZING A PRIVATE MESSAGE
JUJU SENT TO BROWN BACK WHEN HE
WAS IN COLLEGE ASKING FOR TIPS
TAKING HIS GAME TO THE NEXT
LEVEL.
EVEN LE'VEON BELL WAS TWEETING
THIS WITH EVERYBODY REVEALING
HIS OWN TEXT WITH JAMES CONNER,
WITH THEM GETTING ALONG, AND
THEY'RE HAPPY.
KEITH: WE DON'T NEED TO GET
FIRED FOR THAT.
LET'S GET ON THE FIELD AND
CONTINUE THIS CONVERSATION ABOUT
THESE TWO WIDE RECEIVERS.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT ADRIAN BELTRE
WITH HIS NEW QUARTERBACK, DEREK
CARR WITH THE LARDS AND JUJU
SM■ N■■■■
WITH BEN■OETH■■HO'S
THIS■■■■OMING SEASON?■■■■■■■■■■H
ANTONIO BROWN BASED ON WHAT HE
SAID.
THAT SOUND WITH ADAM SCHEFTER,
UNPARALLELED SUCCESS AT THE WIDE
RECEIVER POSITION.
THAT'S ANTONIO BROWN.
FOR THE LAST SIX YEARS IN A ROW,
OVER 100 CATCHES, OVER 1200
YARDS AND AVERAGING AT LEAST
DOUBLE-DIGIT TOUCHDOWNS.1■■■■■■G
THAT TIME.
IS IT A DROP, STEP DOWN AT THE
QUARTERBACK POSITION TO DEREK
CARR?
YEAH,■■■■■■■ HE IS SO GOOD.
I HAVE TO GO WITH A.B.
KEVIN: THE BEST TWEET IN ALL
THIS DRAMA COMES FROM STEELERS
DEFENSIVE END CAM HEYWARD WHO
SAID THIS.
"WITH ALL THIS BEEF, I'VE GOT TO
GO VEGAN NOW."
THAT IS A PERFECT WAY TO TIE
THIS SEGMENT UP, AS WELL.
WE'LL SEE HOW THIS PLAYS OUT IN
KEITH: THIS JUST INTO
"SPORTSCENTER," GOOD NEWS AT
DUKE.
NOT ABOUT ZION WILLIAMSON
DECIDING HE'LL RETURN FOR
ANOTHER SEASON.TRE JONES IS.
JONES MAKING IT OFFICIAL%p TODA,
HE'LL BE BACK FOR THE 2019-2020
CAMPAIGN.
ESPN HAD JONES AS A BORDERLINE
FIRST ROUND PROSPECT IN JUNE'S
NBA DRAFT.
POSTPONE THAT UNTIL 2020.
UCLA KNOW WHO IT WANTS FOR THE
MOST LADY OR TIGER JOB IN
COLLEGE HOOPS.
RICK BARNES, COACH OF THE YEAR.
UCLA HAS OFFERED $5 MILLION A
YEAR PLUS INCENTIVES AND
BONUSES.
BARNES LOVES IT IN XALVE, --
KNOXVILLE, SOURCES SAY, BUT HE
IS DRAWN TO THE PROSP■■
GETTING JOHN WOODEN'S OFFICE AND
OLD JOB.
BACK TO DICKIE V.
I SPENT 10 YEARS WORKING IN L.A.
AND WHAT JOB FROM WHEN GENE
BARTOW HAD IT TO WHEN MURRAY
BARTOW TOOK IT OVER, IT'S LIKE A
SIREN SONG.
NOT MANY COACHES CAN RESIST IT.
DICKIE V.: RICK BARNES LOVES IT
IN TENNESSEE.
HE'S TOLD ME THAT.
HE WAS THE NAISMITH COACH OF THE
YEAR THIS YEAR AND DID A GREAT
JOB.
HOWEVER, UCLA IS ATTRACTIVE.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
ESPECIALLY THE FACT NOW THEY'RE
GOING TO MAKE A COMMITMENT.
MY INSIDE SOURCES TELL ME THE
COMMITMENT IS BIG-TIME.
THERE WILL BE CHARTER FLIGHTS.
ALL KINDS OF RESOURCESABLE
THAT OTHER PEOPLE DO NOT HAVE
AND RICK BARNES WOULD BE A GREAT
HIRE.
IT'S BEEN EMBARRASSING A LITTLE
BIT WHAT'S GONE ON.
THEY'VE BEEN USED BY SCHOOLS,
COACHES, IN THIS WHOLE SELECTION
PR SINCE STEVE ALFORD WHO
THREE OUT OF FIVE YEARS HE WENT
TO THE SWEET 16 AND IT WASN'T
GOOD ENOUGH.
I THINK IF THEY CAN WORK ON THE
CONTRACT, I THINK HE'S HEADING
TO UCLA AND THAT WOULD BE A
GREAT, GREAT HIRE FOR THEM
BECAUSE HE'S NEVER HAD PROBLEMS
ANYWHERE, WITH NCAA.
HE'S WON EVERYWHERE HE'S BEEN.
RICK BARNES WOULD BE A BIG-TIME
WINNER AND TAKE SOME OF THE
EMBARRASSMENT AWAY.
KEITH: THANK YOU, SIR.
STAND BY.
WE'RE SHOWING TAMPA BAY RAYS
HIGHLIGHTS IN A MINUTE.
KEVIN: NO NBA GAMES TONIGHT BUT
WITH THE PLAYOFFS LESS THAN A
WEEK AWAY AND THE CELTICS BEAT
UP, A SOURCE TELLING ADRIAN
WOJNAROWSKI IT'S A STRAINED LEFT
OBLIQUE FOR CELTICS GUARD MARCUS
SMART.
THE HEAD COACH SAID IT WAS A
BRUISE.
SMART SUFFERED THE INJURY IN
LAST NIGHT'S LOSS TO THE MAGIC.
JAYSON TATUM AGGRAVATED A
PRE-EXISTING SHIN INJURY.
HE WAS FINE DURING MORNING■■■■R■
MONTHS -- SIX MINUTES OF ACTION
YESTERDAY.
THE TOP FIVE SEEDS IN THE EAST
ARE SET IN STONE -- MILWAUKEE,
TORONTO AND PHILLY IN THE TOP
THREE.
BOSTON LOCKING UP HOME-COURT
ADVANTAGE AGAINST THE PACERS.
TONY AND MIKE ANSWERING THE
BIGGEST QUESTION IN THE EAST
BEFORE THE PLAYOFFS.
TONY: WHICH TEAM IS THE FAVORITE
TO COF THE EAST AND MAKE
THE NBA FINALS FIVE OR SIX
MONTHS FROM N■E■] EAST IS
AGAIN, THAT THERE ARE
ENOUGH TEAMS TO HAVE GOOD
PLAYOFFS, MULTIPLE■■ SERIES
MULTIPLE ROU
I'M LOOKING AT THE TOP FOUR.
BY THE WAY, I NEED TO GIVE A
LITTLE --
TONY: WHY DO YOU THINK THE EAST
IS GOOD AGAIN?
MICHAEL: INDIANA'S MAINTAINED A
CERTAIN STANDING EVEN THOUGH
VICTOR OSED MO
■■
MILWAUKEE, TORONTO, PHILL
BOSTON ARE REALLY GOOD.
THEY MAY NOT BE AS G AS
GOLDEN STATE BUT THEY'RE AS GOOD
AS ANYONE ELSE.
TONY: DO YOU KNOW WHY THE EAST
ISN'T GOOD ANYMORE?
BECAUSE LEBRON JAMES ISN'T IN IT
ANYMORE.
HE SUFFOCATED THE OTHER PEOPLE.
MICHAEL: HE'S NOT SUFFOCATED
THESE PEOPLE.■
TORONTO, PHILLY AND
WE'RE TO■E MILWAUKEE,
PHILLY,  T
I'LL TAKE PHILLY IN THAT
SECOND-ROUND SERIES.
I'M WANTING TO TAKE P
TONY: YOU'RE GOING TO CHANGE
YOUR MIND 100 TIMES.
MICHAEL: WHAT ABOUT YOU, THEN?
TONY: I DON'T LIKE PHILLY THIS
YEAR.
I'VE SEEN THEM IN BIG GAMES.
I LIKED BOSTON LAST YEAR.
I WANT TO LIKE BOSTON THIS YEAR
BUT I DON'T.
MICHAEL: STAYING WITH MILWAUKEE.
TONY: IÑkÑkRONT
MICHAEL: BOTH OF US ARE BAILING
ON ANTETOKOUNMPO.
TONY: IT'S GOING 16, 19
WEEKS.
MICHAEL: WHAT ELSE ARE YOU GOING
TO DO?
TONY: I'D LIKE TO LEARN HOW TO
HIT A 6-IRON.
MICHAEL: BACK TO YOU.
KE WE GO AGAIN WITH HIM
AND THE GOLF.
INTO "SPORTSCENTER," AARON
RODGERS SPEAKING ABOUT THE
ARTICLE THAT CAME OUT LAST WEEK
CALLING OUT AN ALLEGED RIFT
BETWEEN HIM AND FORMER HEAD
COACH MIKE MCCARTHY.
WE HEAD BACK TO MINNEAPOLIS FOR
CONTINUING COVERAGE LEADING UP
TO THE NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP
GAME.
THIS IS "SPORTSCENTER."d■'2■d  ■
(Client's Voice)
Remember that degree
you got in taxation?
(Danny)
Of course you don't
because you didn't!
Your job isn't doing hard
work...
...it's making them do hard
...and getting paid for it.
(VO)
Snap and sort your expenses to
save over $4■.
QUICKBOOKS. BACKING YOU.
[Happy Birthday music]
♪♪
Don't get mad,
put those years to
work with E*TRADE.
Reese's eggs are back
and we hid them
somewhere you'll never find...
Sike! We put them everywhere.
Grocery stores and
supermarkets, gas stations,
Don't tell your mother.
which we already mentioned...
Dad, it's fine.
We have ALLSTATE.
AND WITH CLAIMRATEGUARD
THEY WON'T RAISE YOUR RATES
JUST BECAUSE OF A CLAIM.
That's why you're my favorite...
I KNOW.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
The final whistle
was just the start...
Of an epic weekend away.
and travel like a champion.
Expedia.
(Ariana)
What is he DOING?
(Vince)
He better not be messing up
our taxes.
and travel like a champion.
(Lisa)
At H&R Block, you have your own
screen so you can see your
credits, deductions and tax
tips!
(Vince)
We need that now.
(Tax Pro)
What?
(Lisa VO) ♪
Know as you go at
H&R Block.
See your credits, deductions
and tax tips.
Block has your back.
♪♪
Introducing freedom from the
bounds of convention...
472 horses of V8
craftsmanship...
Zero to 60 in 3.96 seconds.
It's performance, born of
refinement.
The 2020 Lexus RC F Track
Edition and RC F.
Experience Amazing at your
Lexus dealer.
Your paycheck. Your family
depends on it.
But if something happened
to you... (woosh)
You need life insurance.
And chances are
SelectQuote can get
it for you for under $1
a day.
SelectQuote found
Alec, 38, a
$500,000 policy
for under $23 a month.
SelectQuote found
Kenisha, 37, a
$750,000 policy
for under $23 a month.
SelectQuote's secret? They
impartially shop a select
group of highly rated
companies like these
for your best rates.
Give your family the
security it needs at a
price you can afford.
>> LEFT CORNER, FOR THREE, AND
THE WIN.
OFF THE WINDOW, GOOD.
FOULED THE SHOOTER.
UP, IT IS GOOD.■L■L■L■LC]■L■L■L.
AND VIRGINIA CAVALIERS WILL PLAY
FOR THEIR FIRST NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP.
>> GOT IT!
COLD-BLOODED!■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■O
WHERE NO TEXAS TECH TEAM HAS
GONE BEFORE.
TEXAS TECH AND VIRGINIA EACH
LOOKING FOR THEIR FIRST NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP.
KEVIN: WHAT A RUN SO THEDRED RAS
NEEDED HIS OWN MEDIC TEAM
SATURDAY NIGHT IN THE WIN OVER
MICHIGAN STATE.
HE IS EXPECTED TO PLAY TONIGHT
AGAINST VIRGINIA, REMARKABLE
CONSIDERING HOW IT LOOKED WHEN
HE SPRAINED HIS ANKLE.
HE ALSO TOOK A COUPLE OF SHOTS
TO THE HEAD.
HE DID NOT PRACTICE YESTERDAY.
HE RANKS THIRD AMONG PLAYERS WHO
MADE THE TOURNAMENT BEHIND
BRANDON CLARKE AND TACKO FALL IN
SHOTS MADE.
>> SIGNIFICANT INJURY CONCERN
FOR TEXAS TECH AS 6'10" STARTING
FORWARD TARIQ OWENS IS DEALING
WITHIL SPRAIN.
ACCORDING TO HEAD COACH CHRIS
HE SUFFERED IT IN THE
SECOND HALF AGAINST MICHIGAN
STATE BUT SURPRISINGLY WAS ABLE
TO RETURN TO THE COURT.
WEVER, WHEN HE CAME TO
STADIUM YESTERDAY, HE WAS IN A
WALKING BOOT AND■■OT
PART PRACT
BEARD TF THIS WAS A
NORMAL TURNAROUND, HE WOULD NOT
PLAY.
BUT BECAUSE IT'S THE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP GAME, HE'S
OPTIMISTIC HE'LL BE ABLE TO GO.
THEY WON'T KNOW FOR SURE UNTIL
OWENS WARMS UP PREGAME.
FOR MORE ON TONIGHT'S OPPONENT
FOR TECH, VIRGINIA.
HERE'S LAURA RUTLEDGE.
LAURA: IT'S BEEN A REMARKABLE
JOURNEY IN A YEAR'S TIME FOR
VIRGINIA.
FROM LOSING TO 16-SEED UMBC IN
LAST SEASON'S FIRST ROUND TO NOW
BEING ON THE BRINK OF A NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP.
KYLE GUY TOOK THAT LOSS LAST
YEAR PARTICULARLY HARD.
BUT WANTED IT TO FUEL HIM.
SO HE MADE A PHOTO OF HIM AFTER
THE LOSS, HIS TWITTER AVATAR IN
THE BACKGROUND ON HIS PHONE.
HE WANTED IT TO BE A CONSTANT
REMINDER TO STAY MOTIVATED.
TONIGHT, A WIN WOULD REPLACE
THAT MEMORY AND ALSO GIVE HIM AN
EXCUSE TO REPLACE THAT PICTURE
WITH WHAT HE CALLS A MUCH BETTER
ONE.
AT THE FINAL FOUR, I'M LAURA
RUTLEDGE, ESPN.
KEVIN: THANK YOU SO MUCH.
A 15-YEAR TREND POINTS TO TEXAS
TECH WINNING THIS GAME STARTING
WITH UCONN IN 2000.
FOR EVERY EVENTUAL NATIONAL
CHAMP THAT ENTERED THE TITLE
GAME WITH A BETTER
PER-POSSESSION SCORING MARGIN
THAN THEIR OPPONENT.
THE RED RAIDERS HAVE BEEN
SIGNIFICANTLY BETTER IN THAT
DEPARTMENT THAN VIRGINIA.
RECE D ANCHORING OUR
COVERAGE.
RECE: SOMEBODY'S BEEN READING
JOHN■■ GATHWAY'S COLUMN ON
ESPN.COM.
TONIGHT, THE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP GAME BETWEEN TEXAS
TECH AND VIRGINIA, THE LOWEST
OVER/UNDER IN THE LAST 20 YEARS,
SETTLING AT 118 BETWEEN
TWO DEFENSIVE STALWARTS.
THAT IS NOT TO SAY THERE WON'T
BE STAR POWER ON■■■■ THE FLOOR .
■■■■■■ THE FIRST TIME SINCE 201,
WE'LL HAVE TWO GUYS IN THE TOP
SIX OF THE ESPN DRAFT BOARD
GOING HEAD-TO-HEAD, JARRETT
CULVER OF TEXAS TECH AND
DEUN■ OF VIRGINIA.
GIVE ME AN X-FACTOR FOR TONIGHT?
SETH: I LOOK FOR MATT TO GO
AFTER -- DEFENSIVELY.
ALMOST THREE SME BUT
OFFENSIVELY HE HAS THELITY&zHOOT
BE SURPRISED OUT OFT MOTION
OFFENSE OF TEXAS TECH, THEY PO
HIM UP A LITTLE, GET HIM INTO
THE BLOCK AND LET HIM MAKE
PLAYS.
MATT BE A TOUGH
FACTOR.
JAY: FOR VIRGINIA, IT'S MAMADI
DIAKITE.
HE DOES A GREAT JOB REBOUNDING
AND FINISHING PLAYS.
HE, MOVE HIS FEET AND
HIS ACTIVITY LEVEL, HE'S ABLE TO
KEEP THE BALL ALIVE, CAN KICK IT
OUT.
I THINK DIAKITE WILL■ BIG
■ ■ OR■■ IN THIS■
JAINGS ENERG
EFFO■■■
TARIQ OWENS IS MY X-FACTOR FOR■,
TEXAS TECH, THE JAVALE MCGEE OF
COLLEGE BASKETBALL AND SHOOTS
WELL F■íOUTSIDE.
2.3ñ■ñ■ BLOCKS PER GAME AND HE'S
HUNTER.O HAVE TO GUARD DE'ANDRE■
HIS LEN COULD BOTHER HUN
>>
RECE:
--
JAY: A GLADIATOR FIGHT OUT
■■E.
RECE: WE■■■■■■■■ HAVE X-FACTORSU
GUYS.
THEY WILL MAKE THEIR NATIONAL■■■
CHAMPIONSHIP PICKS AND YOU'LL
MAKE YOURS ALONGSIDE THEM COMING
UP LATER ON "SPORTSCENTER."
ANNOUNCER: "SPORTSCENTER" ON THE
ROAD IS PRESENTED BY ROCKET
MORTGAGE BY QUICKEN LOANS.
CUBS OPENER AT WRIGLEY WHILEED ?
CELLULAR AGAINST BLAKE SNELL OF
THE TAMPA BAY RAYS.
DOWN 3-0 TO WELINGTON CASTILLO.
CHANGEUP, STRIKE TWO.
FROZEN PIZZA.
3-0.
MONCADA AND THE GUY BEHIND HIM
IN THE WHITE SOX PECKING ORDER,
JIMENEZ, WITH THE LINER OFF
SNELL.
AND TIM ANDERSON, FORGIVE ME.
SNELL FAILS TO FIELD THAT
CLEANLY, SAFE AT FIRST.
RUNNERS AT THE CORNER.
GETS JOSE ABREU ON THE CURVE
WITH ONE OUT.
AND THE RAYS ARE 8-3.
THEY LEAD THE YANKEES BY TWO AND
LEAD THE RED SOX BY FIVE.
FIVE!
BARRY SANCHEZ, THREE HOMERS TO
THE YANKEES YESTERDAY.
THEY LOOK TO STAY HOT IN HOUSTON
TONIGHT.
YOU CAN WATCH THAT AT 7:00 ON
ESPN.
THEY HAVE A TOUGH TEST AGAINST
JUSTIN VERLANDER.
GRANDPA ROSSI, DAVID ROSS, HAS
BEEN GOOD ENOUGH TO TAKE A
MOMENT FROM HIS PREP FOR THE
YANKS-ASTROS WHICH HE AND BOOING
SCIAMBI HAVE AT THE TOP OF THE
HOUR, JOINING US.
WHEN I HEARD THE YANKS HIT SEVEN
HOMERS, I ASKED IF THEY HAD WON
OR LOST.
NOW WE'RE HEARING ABOUT SEVERINO
GOING BACK TO NEW YORK FOR AN
M.R.I.
STANTON'S HURT, HICKS IS HURT
AND TULOWITZSKI.
WILL THIS COLLAPSE ON TOP OF
THEM?
DAVID: IF THE YANKEES WANT TO
WIN A WORLD SERIES, THEY'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO GET THOSE GUYS
HEALTHY, ESPECIALLY SEVERINO.
YOU NEED SOMEBODY WHO ANCHOR THE
TOP OF THE STAFF.
RIGHT NOW THEY CAN HOLD DOWN THE
FORT.
YOU SEE THE HOME RUNS THEY'RE
HITTING.
THEY'VE GOT ONE OF THE BEST
BULLPENS MAYBE IN THE HISTORY OF
BASEBALL WITH THE PRODUCT THEY
HAVE SO I THINK THEY'LL BE ALL
RIGHT IN THE REGULAR SEASON.
THEY NEED SOME OF THOSE GUYS
BACK BUT THEY'LL BE ABLE TO HOLD
DOWN THE FORT.
KEITH: VERLANDER LIT UP BY TEXAS
IN HIS LAST START.
ANY CONCERN THERE?
DAVID: NO.
HIS VELOCITY IS STILL THERE.
IT'S JUSTIN VERLANDER, A
CHAIRMAN.
HE DOES HIS HOMEWORK, ONE.
MOST INTUITIVE PITCHERS IN THE
GAME.
HE'LL BE JUST FINE.
KEITH: EVERYBODY'S TALKING ABOUT
CHRIS DAVIS OF THE ORIOLES, JUST
SHY OF THE RECORD FOR AT-BATS
WITHOUT A HIT AT 0-44.
HE'S ALMOST HALFWAY TO 0-87 FROM
BOB UHL.
WHAT DO YOU DO FOR YOU'RE
DAVID: A GUY YOU PAID THAT MUCH
MONEY DOES NO GOOD FOR OUR THE
BENCH.
PLAY OR YOU'LL LET WHETHER HE'LL
HE'S MAK■■ MONEY WHETHER OR
NOT HE'S PLAYING.
HE'S A THREAT IN THE LINEUP.
I KNOW HE'S STRUGGLING BUT IF
YOUR ORGANIZATION HAS CONFIDENCE
IN YOU, THAT CAN TRANSLATE INTO
THE PLAYER.
SOMETIMES THAT'S THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING, HAVING THE
ORGANIZATION ON YOUR SIDE.
HE'S A GUY THEY OWE A LOT OF
MONEY TO AND YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
SEE HIM ON THE BENCH.
THEY'LL RELEASE HIM OR PLAY HIM.
KEITH: DAVID ROSS AND BOOG
SCIAMBI, ASTROS-YANKEES AT THE
TOP OF THE HOUR.
BOTH THESE GAMES ON ESPN AND
ESPN APP SO YOU CAN WATCH
ANYWHERE AND YOU HAD BETTER OR
ROSSI WILL FIND YOU.
>>
ANNOUNCER: "WHAT 2 WATCH 4" IS
BROUGHT TO YOU BY VIVID
CALIFORNIA.
CALIFORNIA, DREAM BIG■X.
KEVIN: THIS JUST INTO
"SPORTSCENTER."
AARON RODGERS SPEAKING ABOUT THE
ARTICLE THAT CAME OUT LAST WEEK
CALLING OUT AN ALLEGED RIFT
BETWEEN HIM AND FORMER HEAD
COACH MIKE MCCARTHY.
RODGERS' RESPONSE IS AHEAD RIGHT
AFTER THIS.
How can you make McDonald's
hot and deliciously
juicy Quarter Pounder
even more delicious?
One word:
Baaaacooooon.
The new fresh beef Quarter
Pounder Bacon or Deluxe.
Two new ways to
leave you speechless.
Pair it with any size soft
drink for just one dollar.
WE DON'T JUST MAKE CARS...
WE MAKE TECHNOLOGY
THAT MOVES PEOPLE
♪
THIS IS THE 2019 NISSAN ROGUE
FEATURING TECH LIKE
PROPILOT ASSIST
IT HELPS KEEP YOU
CENTERED IN YOUR LANE
♪
AND IN CONTROL
THIS IS HOW NISSAN INTELLIGENT
MOBILITY IS REINVENTING DRIVING-
FOR EVERYONE.
NOW THE MOST EXCITING TECH YOU
OWN IS IN YOUR DRIVEWAY
Lowe's knows you
do laundry right.
XXX■>ó>■A
We do it right too,
with select Whirlpool washers
with "Load & Go" dispensers
■7o up to up to
ds between r■;■;
So you can pour it
and ignore it.
NINGOODS] THINK WE'RE GOING
WITH A FAMILY VAN.
A FAMILY VAN?
WAS THAT HER CHOICE?
NAAAH MAN,
THAT WAS MY CHOICE.
THIS THING'S G■SEATS,YER,
IT'S GOT A BUILT-IN
VACUUM CLEANER.
YOU EVER SEEN MY KID
EAT CRACKERS?
YEAH... SO YOU SEE
HOW THAT WORKS?■■555eeee
■&x
SOMETIMES YOU GOTTA GO
STRAIGHT FOR THE SOURCE.
CAR LOANS FAST FROM
NAVY FEDERAL CREDIT UNION...
OUR MEMBERS ARE THE MISSION.
New lower price.
Wow. That's a lot
of asparagus.
Yeah, you said get
a bunch of asparagus.
Oh, you...
bunch.
I... thought you kinda...
What do you get
when you add
lettuce and tomato
bunch.
to McDonalds hot
and deliciously juicy
Fresh Beef
Quarter Pounder?
You get Fresh on
Fresh on Fresh.
The new Fresh Beef
Quarter Pounder
Deluxe
Two new ways to
leave you speechless.
Pair it with any size soft
drink for just one dollar.■7
♪ ♪
This is the family who booked
the trip.
Which led to new adventures
and turned moments into
memories.
With flights, hotels,
activities and more
for your Florida vacation,
Expedia has everything
you need to go.
♪You know I got it♪
♪All I'm askin' is for
a little respect♪
Excuse me Ma'am,
would you like to have my seat?
♪R-E-S-P-E-C-T♪
♪Find out what it
mee♪■■■■
♪Take care. TCB, oh♪
KEVIN: KEVIN AND KEITH BACK WITH
YOU.
OFFSEASON WORKOUTS OPEN TODAY
FOR THE PACKERS AND AARON
RODGERS BACK IN GREEN BAY THISWR
HIM AND FORMER HEAD COACH MIKE
MCCARTHY.
LAST WEEK, MCCARTHY MADE HIS
FIRST EXTENDED COMMENTS ABOUT
BEING FIRED DURING THE SEASON
LAST YEAR TO ESPN'S ROB
DEMOVSKY.
THEN A BLEACHER REPORT CAME OUT
WITH ANONYMOUS SOURCES
CRITICIZING THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN MCCARTHY AND RODGERS.
SOME SAID RODGERS REGULARLY
CRITICIZED MCCARTHY'S PLAY
CALLING AND THAT THE
RELATIONSHIP WAS A CANCER IN THE
LOCKER ROOM AND RODGERS
REPORTEDLY SAID MCCARTHY HAD A
LOW FOOTBALL I.Q.
RODGERS RESPONDED TO THE ARTICLE
A SHORT TIME AGO ON ESPN RADIO
MILWAUKEE.
THIS IS NEW ON "SPORTSCENTER."
>> IT'S NOT A MYSTERY.
THIS WAS A SMEAR ATTACK BY A
WRITER LOOKING TO ADVANCE HIS
CAREER, TALKING WITH MOSTLY
ú ú @@,
!÷E AN AGENDA, WHETH
'RE ADVANCING THEIR OWN
S OR JUST TRYING TO STIR
OLD STUFF UP AND THEN WHAT
HAPPENS,■ ■g SAME TIRED MEDIAFOç
ABOUT IT WHO -- THIS JUST
EMPHASIZES THEIR OPINION ABOUT
ME ALREADY.
SO IT'S JUST -- I
CRAZY THING IS, THERE'S SUPER
SLANTED OPINIONS IN THAT PIECE
STATED AS FACT AND THEN THERE'S
QUOTE/UNQUOTE FACTS WHICH ARE
JUSTES.
SO INE CASES WHERE Y■z■z
IGNORE SOMETHING LIKE THIS OR
GLOSS OVER IT, I DON'T THINK YOU
CAN IN THIS CASE BECA■■ ME
■■d MAIN THESIS POINTS I
WANTED TO TALK ABOUT.
E FIRST IS THE MARK MURPHY
CONVERSATION BECAUSE PART OF THE
ARTICLE■■■■■■■■■■■■ SEE6■6■■■■■,
THE PACKERS ARE■JRIED<4■ Aú■ ME
AS THE LEADER OF THE FOOTBALL
TEAM MOVING F■u
I'M GOING TO SAY TWO THINGS.
ONE,F THEY KNEW THAT, WHY
WOULD THEY OFFER ME A CONTRACT
LAST YEAR.
AND TWO, WHICH GOES TO MY SECOND
CENTRAL THESIS POINT I'M GOING
TO TAKE DOWN, IS, IF I REALLY
DISLIKE MIKE THAT MUCH, WHY
WOULD I RE-SIGN KNOWING IF I
PLAY WELL AND WE DO WHAT WE DO
AROUND HERE, WE MADE THE
PLAYOFFS EIGHT STRAI■ IT@■ HURT.
IT'S GOING TO BE ME AND MIKE MY
ENTIRE CAREER.
IF I DISLIKED HIM THAT MUCH, DO
YOU THINK I'D RE-SIGN?
IS THE MONEY THAT IMPORTANT TO
ME?
I TELL YOU, IT'S NOT.
KEVIN: THAT WAS MOMENTS AGO,
AARON RODGERS ON ESPN MILWAUKEE
RADIO.
TIM HASSELBECK BACK WITH US.
WHAT'S YOUR REACTION TO RODGERS
DEFENDING HIMSELF RIGHT THERE?
TIM: I KIND OF AM LIKE, GOOD FOR
YOU, AARON RODGERS.
HE ALLUDES TO IT, HE COULD
EASILY IGNORE THIS STUFF,
ESPECIALLY THE STUFF HE THINKS
ARE LIES ABOUT HIS RELATIONSHI
■■2 MCCARTHY, BECAUSE
TRUTHFULLY, HOWPWSWPWSWSWUATHEIR
RELATIONSHIP IS LIKE?
I ALSO THINK HE UNDERSTANDS THAT
HE SPENT A LOT OF TIME WITH MIKE
MCCARTHY.
THEY HAD A LOT OF SUCCESS
LE WITH AILE, WHEN■
COACH, THERE IS GOING TO BE
PATCHES WHERE YOU DON'T AGREE
WITH EVERYTHING THAT COACH IS
SAYING, THAT COACH ISN'T GOING
TO AGREE WITH THE PLAYER'S
FEELINGS ON THINGS.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN THAT YOU
DON'T RESPECT THE GUY OR DOESN'T
MEAN THAT YOU -- THERE WEREN'T
GOOD PARTS OF PLAYING FOR THAT
COACH.
SO, YOU KNOW, READING SOME OF
THE STUFF I READ ABOUT MIKE
MCCARTHY IN THE BLEACHER REPORT
ARTICLE, I WOULD SAY THIS.
I KNOW MIKE MCCARTHY, I KNOW
WHAT KIND OF COACH HE IS AND HOW
MUCH FOOTBALL HE KNOWS AND IT
WOULD BE EASY TO FIND BITTER,
ANGRY PLAYERS ON EVERY TEAM TO
SAY NEGATIVE THINGS ABOUT
PEOPLE.
SO I THINK THE CONTEXT OF THAT
MATTERS.
QUITE HONESTLY, I BELIEVE A LOT
OF WHAT AARON RODGERS IS SAYING■
KEVIN: RODGERS IS ONE OF THOSE
TALENTS THAT MANY PEOPLE BELIEVE
HE SHOULD HAVE HAD MORE THAN ONE
LOMBARDI TROPHY WITH MIKE
MCCARTHY.
NEW HEAD COACH FOUR YEARS OLDER
THAN AARON RODGERS.
WHAT'S AT STAKE FOR AARON
RODGERS THIS SEASON AND THE
PACKERS?
TIM: I REMIND PEOPLE, DREW
BREES, PRETTY GOOD, ONE SUPER
BOWL.TO THINK THE BEST QUK IN
THE GAME WINS THE SUPER BOWL
EVERY YEAR, THAT'S NOT HOW IT
S.
WHAT'S AT STAKE IN THEY FIRED
THEIR HEAD CAUSE THEY
NEED THEM TO PLAY BE
THEY WERIR TEAM IN
WHAT'S AT STAKE IS HE NEEDS TO
ARN A NEW OFFEN TO
HELP BE A LEADER OF2;T TE
HELP THEM COMPETE AGAINST THE
BEARS WHO ARE BETTER AND THE
VIKINGS ARE A GOOD TEAM.
THAT'S REALLY WHAT'S AT STAKE
BUT IT'S NOT GOING TO CHANGE THE
WAY PEOPLE FEEL ABOUT HOW GOOD
AARON RODGERS HAS BEEN AND
PROBABLY WILL CONTINUE TO BE.
KEVIN: RODGERS SPEAKING OUT
ABOUT THAT BLEACHER REPORT
ARTICLE ABOUT THE RIFT BETWEEN
HIM AND MIKE MCCARTHY.
THANKS SO MUCH.
KEITH: ONCE UPON A TIME THERE
WAS A 25-YEAR-OLD OUTFIELDER WHO
WON A HOME RUN TITLE ONE YEAR
BUT IF YOU EXTRAPOLATED HOW MANY
HOMERS HE WOULD HIT IN HIS LIFE,
THE MATH WOULD HAVE SAID HE
MIGHT BREAK BABE RUTH'S ALL-TIME
RECORD SO LONG AS HE KEPT AT THE
PACE FOR 26 SEASONS.
THAT GUY BROKE BABE RUTH'S
RECORD.
IT WAS HANK AARON, IT WAS ON
"MONDAY NIGHT BASEBALL" AND ON
RADIO WORLDWIDE ON ARMED FORCES
BROADCASTING.
>> LINE DRIVE INTO DEE■■=év■s■[E
FENCE, IT IS GONE!
WHAT A MARVELOUS MOMENT FOR
BASEBALL.
ATLANTA AND THE STATE OF
GEORGIA.
WHAT A MARVELOUS MOMENT FOR THE
COUNTRY AND THE WORLD.
A BLACK MAN IS GETTING A
STANDING OVATION IN THE DEEP
SOUTH FOR BREAKING A RECORD OF
AN ALL-TIME BASEBALL IDOL.
KEITH: AFTER THE BALL CROSSED
THE FENCE, VIN SCULLY WENT
SILENT AND LET THE CROWD TELL
THE STORY FOR 25 SECONDS.
THE KID IN THE LONG RAIN COAT
WITH THE MICROPHONE BURSTING
INTO THE CELEBRATION AT THE
PLATE IS MY LATE COLLEAGUE,
CRAIG SAGER.
IF YOU THINK HANK AARON ISN'T
STILL THE ALL-TIME HOME RUN
LEADER, THINK AGAIN REAL HARD.
N:UT HOME RUNS.
AARON JUDGE, TOP OF THE HOUR,
GETTING READY FOR A PHENOMENAL
SHOWDOWN IN HOUSTON.
VERLANDER VERSUS TANAKA.
SIGN ME UP.
THAT'S LESS THAN 10 MINUTES
AWAY.
FIRST PITCH ON ESPN.
YANKEES-ASTROS.
STILL TO COME, WE GO BACK TO
MINNEAPOLIS AND TONIGHT'S
NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP GAME.
"COLLEGE GAMEDAY" WITH THEIR
PREDICTIONS.
WHICH TEAM WILL BECOME A FIRST
TIME CHAMPION TONIGHT?
TEXAS TECH OR VIRGINIA?
Huge mistake.
Kevin Harvick?
Choose Mobil 1
Synthetic instead.
It protects engines better
than conventional motor oil.
Yea you would say that,
you're wearing the logo.
How about now?
Get 250,000 miles
of protection.
Upgrade to Mobil 1.
GATORADE ZERO.
ALL THE ELECTROLYTES.
ZERO SUGAR.
♪♪
♪♪■?■■■■■■■2■■■■:
GET MORE OUT OF ZERO.
My insurance rates are probably
gonna double.
But dad, you've got
ALLSTATE.
WITH ACCIDENT FORGIVENESS
THEY GUARANTEE YOUR RATES
WON'T GO UP
JUST BECAUSE OF AN ACCIDENT.
Smart kid.
INDEED.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
my dream car.
It turns out, they want
me to start next month.
She can stay with you to
finish her senior year.
Things will be tight but,
we can ma♪ ♪this work.
Now...
Grandpa, what about
your dream car?
This is my dream now.
Principal we can help
you plan for that .
RUN WITH US.
On a John Deere
X300 Series Mower.
Because seasons change
Wow, ytdone
yourself this time.
but true character doesn't.■
Hey, what're neighbors for?
beautiful.
RUN WITH US.
Search "John Deere X300"
for more.
There's little rest
for a single dad,
and back pain made it hard to
sleep and get up on time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid,
plus the 12 hour pain
relieving strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a Better AM.
ANNOUNCER: "SPORTSCENTER" IS
BROUGHT TO YOU BY HELL BOY, ONE
HELL OF A SUPER HERO.
IN THEATERS FRIDAY.
KEITH: BOOG SCIAMBI AND DAVID
ROSS DOING THEIR■■@ EXERCISES
AS WE SPEAK AS JOSE ALTUVE LEADS
THE ASTROS.
TOP OF THE HOUR ON ESPN.
AFTER THAT, IT'S "SPORTSCENTER"
TONIGHT WITH KENNY MAYNE AND
ZUBIN MEHENTI WITH LIVE POSTGAME
REACTION AND CELEBRATION FROM
THE NCAA NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP
GAME AND WHY JAMES HARDEN IS
UNGUARDABLE AND INSIDE THE
YANKEES' START OF THE SEASON.
DON'T WEAR GOOD SHOES' IF YOU'RE
GOING TO DO THAT.
KEVIN: THE LAST TIME TEXAS TECH
LOST A GAME, MARCH 14.
SECOND ROUND OF THE BIG 12■■■■■
TOURNAMENT, AGAINST WEST
VIRGINIA, A TEAM THAT FINISHED
10 GAMES UNDER .500 IN THE
CONFERENCE.
SATURD■w■÷ NIGHT'S STAR, MATT
ONEY, HELD POINTS IN THE
LOSS.
JARED CULVER FAILED TO HIT A
THREE-POINTER.
IF TEXAS TECH PULLS OFF THE WIN,
THEY'LL BE THE FIRST TEAM IN
NCAA TOURNAMENT HISTORY TO WIN
THE NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP AFTER
LOSING ITS FIRST CONFERENCE
TOURNAMENT GAME.
CANNOT WAIT.
TIME TO PICK A CHAMPION.
BACK OUT TO RECE DAVIS AND THE
REST OF THE "GAMEDAY" GUYS.
RECE: TEXAS TECH AND VIRGINIA
EACH I■■■■■■IRST TITLE
THE FIRST T■&■& FEATURING TWO
FIRST TIMERS SINCE THE FAMOUS
BIRD-MAGIC GAME IN 1979.
WHO WOULD IT BE, TEXAS TECH OR
VIRGINIA?
WEAPFENSIV THEHE DA;NN■TECH HASE
STRETCH.
I GO WITH THE RED RAIDERS.
WHUYS LIKEDN'TME
IN THEIR LAS■>■>LAYED■
WELL DOWN THE STRETCH WHEN YOU
NEED■ ■■
I THINK MATT MOOO MOREmO1G UP.
UP.
I LIKE THE OPTIONS■;AM HAS
DEFENSIVELY.■2■
THEY DISRUPT.
THEY CAN CREATE TURNOVERS WITH
PHYSICALITY AND HAVE MOREAPONS ■
SE■í■b■=■&QEXAS THE■
TECH RED RAIDERS BECAUSE THEY'VE
BEEN THE MOST DOMINANT TEAM IN
THE NCAA TOURNAMENT.■■
TOTAL 70 POINT■S
HOW?%÷■8■8 END.
THEY'LL KEEP VIRGINIA ON ONE
OwR.
'LL PRESSURE THE BASKETBALL.
THEY'LL RUN THEM OFF Tx■■■■■■■■■
THEY'LL MAKE IT HARD FOR THEM TO
CREATEU■■■Ñ■■■ç■■w■■■■sOFFENSE.W
I LIKE TEXAS TECH WINNING THIS
GAME.■@■@
■=TEXAS TECH IS A GREAT
DEFENSIVE TEAM, THEY'VE PROVEN
THAT ALL SEASON LON
BUT ENñ■ñ■■CTHE MOST EFFICM ALL
Ñ■qçqçççINIA AND I
THINK VIRGINIA WILL WIN THIS
BALL GAME.
IT'S GOING TO BE CLOSE BUT THE
DIFFERENCE WILL BE TY JEROME
BECAUSE HE CAN MAKE PLAYS ON HIS
OWN.
IN THAT OFFENSE VIRGINIA LIKES
■■E MOVER BLOCKER÷n÷n
NSE, I TEND TO THINK TY
JEROME WILL HAVE THE BIGGEST
GAME.
IF TEXAS TECH CAN STOP HIM, THE
AND DRIVE THE BALL AGAINST THAT
IA DEFENSE THEN THE RED
RAIDERS WILL WIN.
BUT I VIRGINIA WILL DO IT.
OUR COMRADES HAV
ESTABLISHED VIRGINIA AS A 5-1
FAVORITE TO WIN THE NATIONAL
CHAMPIONSHIP NEXT YEAR.
ON OUR SET, IT'S 2-2.
EVEN MONEY.
KEVIN:PLENTY OF TIME BEFORE TH
GAME TIPS OFF AND BASEBALL
COMING YOUR WAY IN LESS THAN A2
MINUTE.
WHEN BATTING FIRST IN THEINEUP
SINCE 2017.
YANKEES-ASTROS COMING UP ON
ESPN.
KEITH: RYAN SHAZIER AFTER HIS
2017 NIGHTMARE, IN IS THIS PAST
WEEKEND.
THAT'S HIM BOX JUMPING WITH JUST
A LITTLE HELP.
QUOTE SOMEONE FROM HIS
ORGANIZATION FROM MANY YEARS
AGO.
DON'T GIVE UP, DON'T EVER GIVE
UP.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
KEVIN: FANTASTIC.
GOOD LUCK TO THE BETTOR WHO
DROPPED $1500 IN NOV