>> IF YOU WERE GIVEN A VOTE, YOU
WOULD JUST VOTE YOUR ENTIRE
LAKER TEAM.
>> YEAH, BUT I WOULD ALSO VOTE
IN MICHAEL JORDAN, OF COURSE AND
A BUNCH OF OTHER GUY
NK IF YOU MAKE IT
TRANSPARENT LIKE THAT, THEN IT'S
GOING TO BE REALLY■■■■■■■■■■■■■
GUYS THAT DON'T WANT TO TELL YO
MORE SAFER.
SO YEAH, I THINK THE WAY IT IS
RIGHT NOW, JUST DON'T GIVE
VOTE WHEN IT COM■ñW■
AWARD
>> TEAM-WIDE VOTE.
PARENT BY TEAM, NOT BY
PLAYER.
[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
ESPN, INC.]
[CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE,
WHICH IS RESPONSIBLE FOR ITS
CAPTION CONTENT AND ACCURACY.
VISIT NCICAP.ORG]
BOMANI: 9:20 P.M. IS THE TIP
TIME FOR THE GAME.
PABLO: IT WAS 9:20?
THEY COULDN'T GIVE US NINE
FLAT?
BOMANI: THEY COULD NOT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THEY DECIDED
9:20.
PABLO: IS IT THE WEST COAST
BENEFITING HERE?
BOMANI: I GUESS.
ARE THEY FLYING HOME TO GO TO
SLEEP?
PABLO: THEY HAVE WARM WEATHER,
PALM TREES AND EARLY GAMES.
THEY DON'T NEED THIS.
WITH THESE TEAMS?
BOMANI: GOING TO BE A STRUGGLE.
PABLO: YOU HAVE THE FIRST CARD.
BOMANI: I DO HAVE THE FIRST
CARD.
IT IS THE NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP
GAME.
THEY HAVE IT GAMMONS AFTER
BRUCE PEARL'S SQUAD LOST IN
CONTROVERSY.
1.5 SECONDS LEFT.
KYLE GUY PUT UP A MISSED
THREE-POINTER A FOUL WAS
CALLED.
THERE WAS AN ARGUMENT ABOUT
THIS.
WE GOT THIS RIGHT HERE.
PABLO: 1.5 SECONDS.
BOMANI: PEOPLE TRYING TO SAY
THAT WASN'T A FOUL.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE GUY JUMPED.
HOW WAS THAT A FOUL?
PABLO: VERTICAL IS NOT JUST A
ROY HIBBERT RELATED CONCEPT.
THIS IS KIND OF WHAT THE RULE
IS THERE FOR.
BOMANI: WHAT SYMPATHY DO YOU
HAVE FOR AUBURN IN ALL OF THIS?
PABLO: I DON'T HAVE MUCH.
I GET IT WE DON'T WANT TO SEE
THE GAME END THAT WAY.
WE CONTE WANT TO SEE THE
NATIONAL GAME PARTICIPANT
DECIDED BY THREE FREE-THROWS,
WHICH KYLE SANK COOLEY.
BUT THE OTHER THING IS LET'S
JUST NET ENFORCE THE RULES, AND
THE RULES ARE TO BE ENFORCED
WHEN THE REFS CALL IT IN THAT
WAY.
BOMANI: AUBURN MANAGED TO DO
WHAT I THOUGHT WAS IMPOSSIBLE,
WHICH IS TO BLOW A FOUR-POINT
LEAD TO VIRGINIA WITH SEVEN
SECONDS LEFT.
A FOUR-POINT LEAD AGAINST THAT
TEAM IS BASICALLY
INSURMOUNTABLE BECAUSE IT TAKES
THEM SO LONG TO GET ANYTHING
GOING ON OFFENSE.
WE SAW A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO
WITH SYRACUSE PUT THE PRESS ON,
AND THOSE DUDES COULDN'T MAKE
RUNNING LAY-UPS BECAUSE THEY
WERE CAUGHT UP IN THE IDEA OF
MOVING FAST.
THIS FALLS ON BRUCE PEARL
BECAUSE OF THE WAY THEY USED
THOSE FOULS LATE.
IT LOOKED LIKE THEY WERE TRYING
TO USE UP THEIR FOULS TO GIVE
RATHER THAN USE THEM IN THE
PLACE THEY HAD TO.
THAT WAS A COACHING DISASTER.
PABLO: THE GREAT SYMPATHY I
HAVE FOR THEM WAS IN THAT
MISSED DOUBLE DRIBBLE CALL.
THAT WAS EGREGIOUS AND BEFORE
THE THREE-POINTER.
BOMANI: PEOPLE'S DEFENSE FOR IT
IS WHEN YOU DIDN'T SEE IT ON
TV.
LET ME SHOW YOU WHO COMES INTO
THE SHOT RIGHT THERE.
RIGHT THERE, THE REF.
UNLESS HE SNUCK DOWN FROM FOOT
LOOKER, HE IS THE ONE WHO IS
SUPPOSED TO SEE THAT.
PABLO: THE REASON WHY I WANTED
THAT CALLED IS WHAT DO WE HAVE
TONIGHT?
WE HAVE VIRGINIA AND TEXAS
TECH.
WHEN WE TALK ABOUT STYLES OF
FIGHTS, WE SAY IT IS THE
UNSTOPPABLE FORCE VERSUS THE
IMMOVABLE ONLY.
BOMANI: TEXAS TECH, WHICH HAS
POSSIBLY THE BEST DEFENSE WE
HAVE SEEN IN THE LAST 20 YEARS,
OFFENSIVELY I THINK THEY ARE
GETTING A LITTLE BIT OF A BAD
R57.
THEY MOVE THE BALL.
THEY ARE NOT A BAD TEAM TO
WATCH.
THEY HAVE SOME ATHLETIC GUYS
OUT THERE.
BUT IF YOU THINK THEY PLAY
SLOW.
THEY PLAY SEVEN POSSESSIONS A
GAME FASTER THAN VIRGINIA.
VIRGINIA IS THE LITERALLY
SLOWEST TEAM IN AMERICA.
SO WE ARE GOING TO HAVE THE
GREAT DEFENSE OF TEXAS TECH
AGAINST AN OFFENSE THAT KIND OF
HELPS A DEFENSE BECAUSE THERIOT
NOT TRYING TO SCORE THAT MANY
POINTS IN THE FIRST PLACE.
PABLO: YOU DON'T HAVE TO LOVE
THE NBA TO GET THE ARGUMENT I
AM ABOUT TO MAKE, BUT THIS IS
THE STYLE OF MODERN BASKETBALL.
BOMANI: WHY ARE YOU TAKING SO
LONG TO GET ACROSS HALF-COURT?
PABLO: I RECENT THIS ASPECT OF
THE GAME.
TAKING OUR TIME.
THEY ARE GOING TO END UP
TONIGHT WITH 60 OR SO
POSSESSIONS TOTAL BECAUSE THEY
ARE GOING TO TRAIN SECONDS OFF
EVERY POSSIBLE SHOT CLOCK.
THE BEST ADVERTISING FOR THIS
GAME IS PREMISED IN THE THEORY
THAT IT WILL BE CLOSE.
LIKE IT WILL COME DOWN TO THE
LAST MINUTE, IT WILL JUST BE A
LOW-SCORING SLOW GAME.
BOMANI: TO BE FAIR TO VIRGINIA,
THEY HAVE HAD TWO GOOD FINISHES
IN THE LAST TWO GAMES.
SO TUNE IN AROUND 11:45.
PABLO: THE NEXT NAME IS KYLE
KORVER.
HE WROTE ABOUT RACISM AND WHITE
PRIVILEGE.
HE WROTE I KNOW AS A WHITE MAN
I HAVE TO HOLD MY FELLOW WHITE
MEN ACCOUNTABLE.
WHAT WAS THE MOST IMPRESSIVE,
INTERESTING THING KORVER SAID
IN ALL OF THIS?
BOMANI: I THOUGHT IT WAS
THOUGHTFUL.
THERE IS A CERTAIN IRONY IN
WHAT MAKES THIS IMPRESSIVE.
WHAT MAKES THIS IMPRESSIVE IS
IT IS DONE BY A PERSON WHO
POSSESSES WHITE PRIVILEGE.
WE ARE LISTENING TO KYLE KORVER
SAY THINGS THAT A LOT OF OTHER
PEOPLE HAVE HAD TO SAY, BUT HE
IS SAYING IT.
I THOUGHT THE WAY HE SAID IT
STOOD OUT.
THE OTHER THING THAT STOOD OUT
WAS HE LOW KEY SAID WE SHUT THE
DOOR IN THE LOCKER ROOM AND
SAID A THESE OTHER GUYS WHO
PLAYED IN UTAH, WHEN THEY
DIDN'T PLAY IN UTAH, THEY HATED
PLAYING IN UTAH.
PABLO: HE TALKED ABOUT BEING
TEAMMATES WITH THABO SEFOLOSHA,
ONE OF THE GUYS THEY WERE
TALKING ABOUT.
HE WAS TALKING ABOUT THABO
SEFOLOSHA AND WHEN HE HAD HIS
INCIDENT WITH POLICE, THE
POLICE BRUTALITY CASE IN NEW
YORK, KORVER SAID HE THOUGHT IF
IT WAS NOT HIM OUT THERE, HE
WOULD NOT HAVE BEHAVED THAT
WAY, THAT THIS WAS A THABO
SEFOLOSHA INCIDENT.
THAT IS A LEVEL OF ADMISSION
THAT HE DID NOT HAVE TO GIVE.
PABLO: THIS GUY THAT SPEAKS ALL
THESE LANGUAGES, GOT JAMMED UP
BY THE COMES, AND MY FIRST
THOUGHT WAS I WONDER WHERE HE
DID.
TO ACKNOWLEDGE THAT PART, YOU
FIGURE STUFF OUT.
THIS IS THE BEAUTIFUL THING
ABOUT THE NBA.
IT TOOK KYLE KORVER A LITTLE
LONGER TO FIGURE THIS OUT, BUT
IN THE NBA THERE SEEMS TO BE A
CULTURAL EXCHANGE THAT TAKES
PLACE THAT IS DIFFERENT THAN
OTHER AMERICAN SPORTS IN THAT
THERE IS A LEVEL OF DISCOURSE
THAT HAPPENS AMONG THE PLAYERS
THAT WE ARE NOT HEARING NEARLY
AS MUCH SAY COMING OUT OF THE
NFL WHEN IT COMES TO THESE
MATTERS.
FOR KORVER TO SAY THESE THINGS
THE WAY HE DID, AND TO SAY IT
TO A BROADER AUDIENCE AND
SAYING THESE ARE THE THINGS WE
NEED TO DO.
THE PEOPLE WHO LOVE THIS
ARTICLE, ARE THEY GOING TO
RE-TWEET IT, OR THEY ACTUALLY
GOING TO LIVE THE STUFF HE
SAID.
I SAW A LOT OF THIS MOVED ME
AND ME ME THINK, BUT WHAT WILL
IT MAKE YOU DO?
PABLO: THIS IS THE WAY AMERICAN
DISCOURSE WORKS.
WE HAVE A GUY LIKE ASHTON KU
CHER SAYING THIS.
THIS HAS BEEN ATTEMPTED BY
BLACK PEOPLE FOR A VERY LONG
TIME.
THERE IS A LOT WITHOUT ANY OF
THE EXIT RAMPS SO WE COULD
FOCUS ON THE MENTAL.
SPEAKING OF THE MESSAGE, THERE
WAS A CONVERSATION WITH HIS
FELLOW PLAYERS.
ROLL THE VIDEO.
WE HAVE THEM CHIMING IN THAN
OUGHT JAZZ ORGANIZATION.
>> IF THEY CAN CREATE THE
THING, SHE CAN HOP ON THE PHONE
WITH 29 OTHER OWNERS AND OTHER
SPORTS OWNERS AND TRY TO HOLD
THEM ACCOUNTABLE.
I THINK IT IS UP TO THE PLAYERS
TO HOLD THE ORGANIZATION
ACCOUNTABLE.
BOMANI: HE IS ON TO SOMETHING
THERE IN THE SENSE THAT --
AGAIN WHAT THIS KYLE KORVER
THINGS DEMONSTRATES IS SOME
PEOPLE MIGHT LISTEN TO ME.
MORE PEOPLE WILL LISTEN TO KYLE
KORVER, AND A HELL OF A LOT
MORE PEOPLE WILL LISTEN TO THIS
RICH OWNER.
IF YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE THE
MESSAGE CHANGE, IT PROBABLY HAS
TO COME FROM THE PEOPLE WHO
HAVE THE REAL POWER.
WAR THEY GOING TO DO BECAUSE
THEY ARE TOO AFRAID OF
OFFENDING THE CUSTOMERS TO MAKE
THEM ACT BETTER.
.STEP ONE IS CLARITY ON THE
ISSUE.
BOMANI: NEXT NAME IS PAUL
PIERCE.
HE SAID THIS WEEKEND ON INSIDE
COUNTDOWN THAT HE HAD A BETTER
CAREER THAN DWYANE WADE.
BO
[LAUGHTER]
>> NBA FINALS MLB.
YOU HAVE HIM IN CAREER POINTS.
HE HAS MORE PLAYOFF POINTS.
PAUL, WHO IS THE BETTER NBA
PLAYER?
>> THAT IS EASY.
I CAN SAY THAT OFF THE BAT.
THAT IS ME.
IF YOU GIVE ME LEBRON, WE GOT
THAT LATE.
EARLY IN MY CAREER, IF YOU GIVE
ME THESE GUYS EARLY IN MY
CAREER --
>> WHAT WOULD HAVE BEEN A
PERFECT TIME FOR YOU?
>> WHEN I AM 24 YEARS OLD, GIVE
ME SHAQ.
GIVE ME LEBRON AND BOSH.
I WOULD BE SITTING ON FIVE OR
SIX CHAMPIONSHIPS EASY.
PABLO: THIS WAS DELUSION
WRAPPED IN SINCERITY, WRAPPED
IN IRONY, BECAUSE THEY SET UP
PAUL PIERCE TO GIVE THAT TAKE.
BUT PAUL PIERCE LOVED GIVING
THAT TAKE BECAUSE HE BELIEVES
THAT TAKE.
BOMANI: WHO SET PAUL PIERCE UP?
LIKE HE JUST SHOWED UP OUT OF
THE CAR AND LANDED ON A
TELEVISION SET AND THEY WERE
LIKE THIS IS WHAT WE ARE GOING
TO TALK ABOUT.
HE KNEW DAMN WELL WHAT THEY
WERE GOING TO TALK ABOUT BEFORE
THEY GOT UP THERE, AND HE MEANT
EVERY WORD.
PAUL PIERCE IS AN ALL-TIME
GREAT PLAYER.
WHEN HE SAYS LOOK AT WHAT
NECESSARY GAVE ME EARLY IN MY
CAREER, I PRESUME HE IS TALKING
ABOUT GUYS LIKE ANTOINE WALKER.
YOU KNOW WHO THE SECOND LEADING
SCORER WHEN THE HEAT WON THE
CHAMPIONSHIP, IN THE NBA
FINALS, THE LEADING SCORER WAS
ANTOINE WALKER.
SHAQ SCORED ALL OF 13.POINTS A
GAME IN THAT SERIES.
COME ON, MAN.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
PABLO: DOES IT SEEM TO BE ABOUT
THE HEAT AND THE CELTICS?
THE HEAT CAME ALONG, AND THEY
WON THE ARMS RACE.
THEY BLEW THE CELTICS OUT OF
THE WATER.
BEFORE PAUL PIERCE USED TO BE
ABLE TO LEAN ON THE IDEA, THE
TSUNAMIER TEAM WAS SOMETHING,
BUT THEY GOT OUTGUNNED.
NOW EACH THE HEAT LOOK MINOR
AFTER WHAT THE WARRIORS ARE
DOING.
WHY IS PAUL PIERCE SAYING I AM
SO GREAT?
BOMANI: IF YOU ASK PAUL PIERCE
WHO IS BETTER ME OR LAKE, HE
COULD COME BACK AND SAY IF YOU
GIVE ME OTHERS I WNBA HERE.
COMING UP, ANTONIO BROWN
Great news, Liberty
Mutual customizes...
Uh uh, I deliver the
news around here.
Sources say Liberty Mutual
customizes your
car insurance, so you only
pay for what you need.
Over to you, logo.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
It is nice.
Yeahare we
a van family?
(Pacifica Talks)
Are we a van family?
Of course you are!■■■■■
Sales guy, gimme your foot.
Is it magic? No.
It's a Pacifica.
Come on in.
Allow me to do a
little self-promosh.
Check out all these features
that I got up in here.
It also comes in a hybrid.
Yo, what's up?
Van life! You know you want it.
What are you waiting for?
Let's get on the road.
But does it ever shut up?
Drive me off the lot baby,
I will sing to you
on the way home.
♪ Pacificaaaaa! ♪
♪ ♪
■■V■ ■■■■■R■■■♪ ♪■hhh
(chime)
♪ ♪
Open an E*TRADE Premium Savings
Account
and earn 2.1% APY on your money.
That's over 20 times the
national average!
♪ ♪
Lowe's knows you
do laundry right.
We do it right too,
with select Whirlpool washers
with "Load & Go" dispensers
go up to oads b r
So you can pour it
and ignore it.
I switched to Liberty Mutual,
because they let me
customize my insurance.
And as a fitness junkie,
I customize everything,
like my bike, and my calves.
Liberty Mutual customizes
yournly     for what you.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>> HIGH NOON IS BEAMED TO YOU
FROM ABOVE THE HEINEKEN RIVER
DECK AT PIER 17.
BOMANI: LAST NIGHT IN THE
WOMEN'S NATIONAL CHAMPIONSHIP
GAME, ARIKE OGUNBOWALE, I HATE
WHEN I STRUGGLED WITH NAMES,
BUT SHE TRIED TO MAKE THE FIRST
ONE, MISSED IT, TRIED TO MISS
THE SECOND ONE, MADE IT.
PABLO: THE GAME ENDS LIKE THAT.
ONE OF THE MOST DECORATED
CLUTCH SHOOTERS EVER HAS AN
EXIT THAT LEADS TO HARD BREAK.
BOMANI: DON'T GET THIS TWISTED.
THE SHOT THEY MADE LAST YEAR
STILL MATTERS.
PABLO: FIRST QUOTE.
A -- AVENATTI LIST ADD DROP BOX
THAT INCLUDED NAMES WILLIAMSON
AND BOL.
BOMANI:, I ASK YOU WHY IS THIS
DROP BOX NOT MAKING A BIGGER
SPLASH?
BOMANI: I SAID THAT AVENATTI
WAS ON A SLOW WALK TO ZION
WILLIAMSON.
THAT WAS THE ONLY THING THAT
COULD MAKE-A-WISH A SPLASH OUT
OF THIS.
HE GOT THERE.
I WAS WONDERING IF HE WAS
HOPING DUKE WOULD BE IN THE
FINAL FOUR.
THIS DUDE IS OUT HERE WITH
DOCUMENTS.
NOBODY SEEMS TO CARE.
PABLO: HE HAS DOCUMENTS WITH
NAMES OF PLAYERS ON THEM.
IN PAST CASES WHEN IT COMES TO
GOVERNMENT STUFF, THEY HAVE
ALWAYS REDACTED THOSE NAMES.
NOW WE HAVE ALLEGED PROOF WITH
A CLARITY WE DON'T OFTEN AGAIN
THAT MAKES ME WONDER.
IS THIS GUY JOSE CANSECO FOR
COLLEGE BASKETBALL?
IS HE THE GUY SO EASILY
DISCREDITABLE, BUT GENERALLY
CORRECT?
BOMANI: THING IS JOSE CANSECO
DIDN'T HAVE PAPERWORK.
RICK PITINO LOST HIS JOB BEHIND
STUFF LIKE THIS.
IN THE END WHERE WE ARE IS
PEOPLE DON'T WANT TO LOOK INTO
THIS IN LARGE PART BECAUSE THEY
LIKE THE DUDE ZION.
IF YOUR ATTITUDE IS SO LAISSEZ
FAIRE ABOUT WHAT AVENATTI IS
BRINGING, YOU NEED TO KEEP THAT
ENERGY ALL TIME.
THE NEXT TIME THE NCAA WANTS TO
JACK A KID UP OR OTHERS, YOU
NEED TO BE STANDING UP AND
SAYING HOW RIDICULOUS THIS IS.
WHAT ANNOYS ME IS SOME OF US
FOR YEARS HAVE BEEN STANDING ON
TABLES SCREAMING HOW UNFAIR
THIS IS, ABOUT HOW THE PLAYERS
ARE BEING OSTRACIZED AND
MISTREATED BECAUSE OF ALL THIS.
NOW ALL OF A SUDDEN YOU DON'T
CARE?
THEN START CARING ABOUT THE
PART THAT MATTERS, WHICH IS
ATTEMPTING TO KEEP THESE KIDS
BROKE.
PABLO: IF YOU ESTABLISH A
CONSENSUS THIS IS ACTUALLY
GOING ON WITH HIGH LEVEL
PLAYERS EVERYWHERE, THEN
THEORETICALLY THE ARGUMENT
BECOMES HARDER TO MAKE WHEN YOU
ARE TRYING TO ARGUE AGAINST
PAYING PLAYERS.
THEY ARE ALREADY BEING PAID.
DO YOU WANT TO LET THE BACK
MARKET DO THE JOB?
BOMANI: PEOPLE THOUGH THINK
PLAYERS SHOULD BE PAID LIVE IN
A BUBBLE AND DON'T REALIZE THE
MAJORITY OPINION REMAINS THAT
THEY SHOULD NOT BE PAID.
QUOTE, EMOTION.
FUMBLED THE POSTSEASON IN THE
BIGGEST GAME OF THE YEAR.
TWEETED ANTONIO BROWN IN
RESPONSE TO A FAN'S TWEET
SAYING JUJU SMITH-SCHUSTER WAS
THE STEELERS' MOST VALUABLE
PLAYER IN 2018.
JUJU THEN TWEETED THIS ABOUT
A.B.
ALL I EVER DID WAS SHOW THAT
MAN LOVE AND RESPECT FROM THE
MOMENT I GOT TO THE LEAGUE.
I WAS GENUINELY HAPPY FOR HIM
TOO WHEN HE GOT TRADED TO
OAKLAND WITH A BIG CONTRACT.
NOW HE IS TAKING SHOTS AT ME ON
SOCIAL MEDIA?
PABLO, WHOSE SIDE ARE YOU ON
HERE?
PABLO: I GUESS I AM WITH JUJU
SMITH-SCHUSTER BECAUSE THE
START WAS SOMETHING ELSE.
THEY WERE TARIK BACKGROUND
RANDOM PITTSBURGH STUFF.
THEN ANTONIO GETS ON THERE WITH
JUJU SMITH-SCHUSTER.
JUJU WAS NOT INVOLVED, AND
BROWN SAW THAT AND SAID THIS
RESONATES WITH ME BECAUSE I
RECENT THIS MAN FOR BASICALLY
HAVING A BETTER REPUTATION THAN
ME DESPITE MAKING MORE MISTAKES
ON THE FIELD.
THUS WE HAVE WHAT WE HAVE
TODAY.
BOMANI: I AM ON NOBODY'S SIDE.
I AM ON THE SIDE OF THE AMISH,
PEOPLE WHO EXISTED PRIOR TO THE
TECHNOLOGY.
SOMETIMES I WANT TO GO AMISH,
IF WE ARE, WE DON'T HAVE TO DO
WITH THIS.
THERE AIN'T NOTHING TO SAY BACK
ON THIS ON THE INTERNET.
EITHER CALL HIM AND TALK TO HIM
OR DON'T.
YOU DON'T NEED TO WORRY ABOUT
WHAT THIS DUDE INTHS BECAUSE
HIS OPINION IS CLEARLY ERRATIC.
FOR ANTONIO BROWN, HOW CAN I BE
ON HIS SIDE ON THIS MATTER,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU SEE SAY
THAT DUDE DROPPED THE BALL IN
THE POSTSEASON.
BRUH, YOU DIDN'T SHOW UP AT ALL
IN WEEK 17.
WHY ARE WE TALKING ABOUT ANY OF
THIS?
ARE
PABLO: AND HE STARTED THE DAY
BY SAYING KEEP YOUR EMOTIONS
OFF THE INTERNET.
AND JUJU SMITH-SCHUSTER HITS
HIM WITH THAT ON TWITTER.
DON'T ARGUE WITH A MILLENNIAL
WHOSE DOG HAS AN AGENT.
BOMANI: I DON'T KNOW WHY HE DID
ME LIKE THAT.
WHO CARES WHY HE DID YOU LIKE
THAT?
PABLO: LAST QUOTE.
THE PERSON THAT LOSES IS THE
PLAYER.
SAID NICK SABAN ABOUT ANYONE
BUT THE TOP RANKED PLAYERS
LEAVING EARLY FOR THE NFL.
LET'S WATCH.
>> I THINK IN THE LAST FIVE
YEARS, NOT COUNTING THIS YEAR,
THERE HAVE BEEN 380 PLAYERS GO
OUT AERIAL FOR THE DRAFT, AND
25% OF THOSE GUYS DIDN'T GET
DRAFTED.
ANOTHER 25% WEREN'T ON A TEAM
IN THREE YEARS.
THAT MEANS 50% OF THE GUYS WHO
WENT OUT EARLY FOR THE DRAFT
HAD FAILED CAREERS.
NOW YOU HAVE GUYS THAT HAVE NO
DRAFT GRADES, SEVENTH ROUND
GRAPES, FREE AGENT PHRASE,
FIFTH ROUND GRADES GOING OUT TO
THE DRAFT.
PERSON THAT LOSES IS THE
PLAYER.
LOOK, I AM 100% NFL.
I AM 100% GUYS HAVING CAREERS.
BUT PEOPLE HAVE TO BE SMART
ABOUT THE BITS DECISIONS THEY
MAKE RELATIVE TO THE NFL
BECAUSE IT IS ALL BUSINESS.
PABLO: BO, WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF
SABAN THERE?
BOMANI: HE IS NOT WRONG
NECESSARILY.
THIS DEPENDS ON POSITION.
IF YOU ARE A RUNNING BACK, YOU
SHOULD GO OUT THERE OR NOT, IT
IS JUST TOO RISKY.
TAKING INTO ACONTI THESE GUYS
COMING OUT OF S.E.C. SCHOOLS,
THEIR MEDICALS ARE AWFUL WHEN
THEY GET TO THE LEAVE.
YOU CAN'T TAKE THOSE HITS FROM
FREE.
HE IS COMING FROM A PERSPECTIVE
WHERE HE IS TRYING TO MAXIMIZE
GUYS' LONG-TERM EARNINGS.
MY QUESTION IS HOW MANY OF THEM
NEED MONEY ON THE SHORT TERM?
THE IDEA OF LEAVING COLLEGE TO
GO GET A JOB, PEOPLE DO THIS
ALL TIME.
FOOTBALL PLAYERS AREN'T
NECESSARILY DIFFERENT.
PABLO: RONNIE HARRISON, A SABAN
FORMER PLAYER, KILLED HIM ON
TWITTER.
KEEP MY NAME OUT OF YOUR MOUTH.
WHAT HE IS TALKING ABOUT IS THE
COSTS.
THE LACK OF INCOME, MAYBE
SOMETHING HAPPENS TO MY
POSITION OR THE TEAM WITH DRAFT
ME.
IT IS NOT ALL THAT SIMPLE.
BOMANI: IT IS FAIR TO SAY THAT
HE DID NOTE IF YOU ARE A SECOND
OR THIRD ROUND PICK AND THERE
IS NO CHANCE YOUR GRADE IS
GOING TO GO UP, YOU MAY AS WELL
GO.
COMING UP NEXT, WHO IS THE MOST
FEARED PLAYER IN THE NBA?
>> WHO IS FEELING CRAFTY?
LOWE'S, HURRY
New lower price.
Wow. That's a lot
of asparagus.
Yeah, you said get
a bunch of asparagus.
Oh, you...
A bunch.
I... thought you kinda...
Incomparable design
makes it beautiful.
State of the art technology
makes it brilliant.
The visionary Lexus NX.
Lease the 2019 NX 300 for
$359 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
Lowe's knows you're a
DI by treating your yard.ats f
■ ■■
We do it right, too.
With the right
plants for your region.
So, you stay a step ahead
of spring all season long.
We got no free pass.
Everything we have,
we've earned.
The unmistakable Lexus IS.
Lease the 2019 IS 300 for
$329 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
You'vete t
■é=é=x;■7HH■■o>■=■■
Yeah, I've had some pretty
prestigious jobs over the years.
News producer,
executive transport manager,
and a beverage distribution
supervisor.
■/■■ñ7■7■7ñ7ñ7■7ñ7■7■7
Now I'm a director
at a security software firm.
Wow, you've been
at it a long time.
Thing is, I like working.
What if my retirement plan
is I don't want to retire?
Then let's not create
a retirement plan.
Let's create a plan
for what's next.
I like that.
Get a plan that's right for you.
TD Ameritrade.
♪♪
What if I wielded the power of
the Infinity Gauntlet...?
I could bend reality to my will,
with a snap of my fingers!
I just saved money with GEICO.
I saved hundreds of dollars!
Nice!
That is a lot of money.
The power is exhilarating!!
HAHAHAHAHAHA! Hah. Ha.
Just got something in my throat.
Yea...
Marvel Studio's "Avengers
Endgame." In theaters April 26.
>> THE PICKS.
WHAT IS THAT?
>> NO, NO, WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
>> I AM ROOTING FOR TEXAS TECH
TOO.
>> SO AM I.
>> WHY NOT?
BOMANI: DO PEOPLE WHO WATCH
WRESTLING GET SENSITIVE WHEN
YOU JOKE ABOUT THAT STUFF?
>> THEY DO BECAUSE IT IS STILL
KIND OF REAL TO THEM.
BOMANI: DID YOUR FRIENDS WHO
WATCH WRESTLING GO TO HARVARD
TOO?
>> THEY DID.
A LOT OF TUA WRITINGS VERY
WISELY SPENT.
TODAY ET CETERA NUMBER, 43.8%,
THE PERCENTAGE WHO SAID JAMES
JOHNSON.
THE KUO WAS WHO DON'T YOU WANT
TO FIGHT?
IS JAMES JOHNSON THE PERSON YOU
WOULD LEAST WANT TO FIGHT?
BOMANI: NUMBER ONE ON THE LIST.
HE IS TRAINED IN THE HI-YAH
YARDS.
HIS DAD AND MOM KNOW HI-YAH.
HE IS WELL TRAINED AND 6'9" ON
TOP OF.
THAT YOU DON'T WANT THOSE
PROBLEMS.
THE PROBLEM IS YOU ARE NOT
GOING TO FIND CLIPS OF JAMES
JOHNSON FIGHTING SOMEBODY IN
THE NBA BECAUSE HE WOULD KILL
SOMEBODY IF HE DID, AND
APPARENTLY THE STREETS NOW.
PABLO: NUMBER TWO WAS STEVEN
ADAMS, 19.8%.
WE HAVE VIDEO OF HIM BEING
IMMOVABLE.
BOMANI: THE QUESTION WAS WHO
DON'T YOU WANT TO FIGHT, NOT
WHO IS THE TOUGHEST.
I THINK ADAMS GOT WHO TOUGH
TEST.
CHARLES OAKLEY AND RON ARTEST
ARE STILL GETTING STROTES.
CHARLES OAKLEY GOT AS MANY
VOTES AS BOBBY PORTIS.
WHO DID HE VOTE FOR, MIROTIC,
WHO DID HE VOTE FOR?
PABLO: I THINK WE KNOW THE
ANSWER.
IS THAT VINCE CARTER HAVING
PTSZ?
BOMANI: WHO IS LEFT IN THE
LEAGUE?
CHARLES OAKLEY RETIRED IN 2004.
PABLO: AND YET HIS SPIRIT
REMAINS WITH US STILL.
BOMANI: I WOULD BE SCARED TO
FIGHT HIM.
IN CLOSING, A LET OF MY FRIENDS
WERE IN TOWN THIS WEEKEND.
THEY DIDN'T CALL ME TO HANG OUT
THOUGH.
HUH-UH.
THEY WERE TOO BUSY GETTING
READY FOR "WRESTLEMANIA."
APPARENTLY THEY WOULD RATHER DO
STUFF LIKE THIS.
THERE IS THE PARKING LOT AT
"WRESTLEMANIA."
PABLO: OH, MAN.
[LAUGHTER]
BOMANI: THAT IS CONCRETE DOWN
THERE.
PABLO: IN BUFFALO WHEN THEY DO
THIS, THERE IS SNOW AND STUFF.
BOMANI: WOW.
COME ON, MAN.
PABLO: I KNOW THAT GUY IS
THEORETICALLY PLAYING IT, BUT
IF YOU TOLD ME HE WAS
PARALYZED, I WOULD BELIEVE
THAT.
BOMANI: WHO IS SHOWING UP IN
THE FOOTLOCKER SUIT TO
"WRESTLEMANIA"?
WOW.
PABLO: THAT IS BASICALLY LIKE
SHOWING UP IN A KOBE JERSEY AT
THIS POINT.
THE REFEREES ARE ESSENTIAL TO
THE ENTERPRISE.
WE TURNED DOWN TICKETS TO
"WRESTLEMANIA."
BOMANI: WE DID.
I CAN'T BE OUT THERE EIGHT
HOURS WATCHING "WRESTLEMANIA."
I WISH WE COULD TAKE THE TIME
AND GO THROUGH THE PHOTOS AND
COUNT THE WEDDING RINGS.
I WANT TO TALK TO THE WOMEN
MARRIED TO THESE DUDES.
HOW DO THEY FEEL ABOUT THIS?
PABLO: ALL I KNOW IS THERE WAS
TOO MUCH TIME SPEPT IN
PARKING LOTS.
THAT VINDICATED MY DECISION NOT
TO GO.
THE ONLY THING WORSE THAN DOING
THIS IS BEING TRAPPED WITH THE
PEOPLE DOING THIS AFTER THE
GAME.
BOMANI: WHAT IS THIS?
MANIA?
PABLO: A SPECTACLE.
IN CLOSING, I WOULD LIKE TO
SHOW YOU THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
THE LETTER OF SUBWAY LAW AND
THE SPIRIT OF SUBWAY LAW.
LET'S WATCH.
PABLO: THERE IS A RULE ON THE
SUBWAY THAT YOU CAN BRING A DOG
ON THE TRAIN IF YOU HAVE YOUR
DOG IN A BAG.
AND THAT IS A AMEZAGA IN
SOMETHING BAG-LIKE.
BOMANI: ON A STRING.
PABLO: THE CONDUCTOR IS LIKE
NO, YOU CANNOT OPERATION DUMBO
DROP INTO MY TRAIN.
NO, YOU CANNOT DO THAT.
BO, YOU ARE A SUBWAY RIDER WITH
MORE DILIGENCE THAN ME.
DO YOU HAVE SYMPATHY FOR ANY OF
THE