What's my favorite
color today?
Pink.
Yup.
(announcer)
But Corey seems to be the pain
in their ass that won't go away.
Chad and Nicole's relationship
is moving to the next level,
taking each other's
measurements.
Wow, you (bleep) it up.
I had it.
No, here.
I got it.
I'm gonna measure it for you,
you (bleep) ding-a-ling.
(announcer)
Janelle's still running hot
after attacking Diandra
for kissing her ex Darian.
And Farrah's discovering her
ripped-up posters,
which was payback by Nurys
for being kicked in the cooter.
Oh, my God.
Someone came up here
and (bleep) up my signs.
All right, so that's
the (bleep) you started!
Did she (bleep) do this?
She might have
did it, Farrah.
Okay.
Well, this is the best one.
Did someone
(bleep) up my-- okay.
All right.
Farrah, let th■■óo■
Don't attack all of my amazing,
amazing signs...
that my housemates spent
their time on making for me.
Did someone have an idea
to (bleep) bend all my signs?
I (bleep) did! I did!
I happily (bleep) did!
I did, I did, I did, I did!
Nurys did!
She kicked me.
She decided to put
her hands on me,
so I grabbed her
"free Farrah" posters
and I ripped them in half.
Stop! No!
You think I give a (bleep)?
No, no, no, no!
Nurys, no!
Diandra, Diandra!
I know!
If you wanna touch my stuff,
your (bleep) gets
a big "(bleep) you"
down the toilet.
Okay, touch my (bleep), bitch.
Touch it, I dare you.
■■uch somebody else's
(bleep).
(Nurys)
I did.
You ugly-ass bitch!
Oh, I'm ugly, bitch?
How much plastic surgery
have you had to fix your face
and your body?
I haven't done not one thing
to my body or my face
and I'm (bleep) gorgeous,
so (bleep) my (bleep), bitch.
(Farrah)
You (bleep)
disgusting bitch.
Sure, sure,
I'll take your (bleep).
I'll take your (bleep)
and put it in the toilet.
If she touches my (bleep),
I'm letting you guys know,
I'ma beat this bitch's ass.
Go ahead, Farrah.
Put that (bleep)
in the toilet.
?? sis.
Here it goes.
Here it (bleep) goes.
Come on, sis.
Here it goes.
Put that (bleep)
in the toilet.
She (bleep) bent every one.
She (bleep) your ex, sis!
(laughter)
She bent! She bent!
Disrespect me,
disrespect my stuff,
you will not be respected.
And, um, karma's a bitch.
Oh, (bleep)!
She ripped her (bleep).
Here we go. Here it goes.
Here you go.
Farrah's said
she ripped it all up.
If you argue with Farrah,
she will kick you in the vagina
and put your in the toilet
and flush.
That's some pussy-ass (bleep).
I've never done something
so crazy like that.
It's bad enough that Farrah
already kicked me in the vagina.
Now she's grabbing my sneakers
and she flushes them
down the toilet.
I could've touched her makeup
that was there,
or any of her personal
belongings, and I didn't,
because I have some type
of class.
Don't threaten me!
Don't trip me!
Don't (bleep) attack me!
(announcer)
Since fighting is
a big fat no-no,
Janelle, Nurys, and Farrah are
sent to hotels for the night
with a warning.
Talk (bleep),
get hit, bitch.
■■■
I'll see you tomorrow
'cause we always
keepin' positive things.
I love you. Mwah!
Love you too.
♪♪
You guys think the, like,
Farrah-Nurys situation
c■c■is gonna continue today or--
Oh, yeah, 100%.
She's in a very precarious legal
situation right now.
Don't be coming around
kicking anyone.
But, like, I just got--
like, this is childish.
Okay, but if you got
kicked in the cooter,
what would you (bleep) do?
I'ma kick you back
in the cooter.
Farrah went back,
and then the security
guard was there.
She tripped over his feet
and Farrah fell on her ass.
Well, good thing she's got
airbags back there.
No, she-- yeah.
Did she bounce?
(laughter)
♪♪
It's not cool, man.
Not cool a
A>ú■■  her in the vagina
for no reason,
it's (bleep) up.
It's what I'm saying, man.
Honestly, because she
done startp)
since day one.
Stirring up the pot,
spreading rumors,
calling me dirty (bleep).
It's-- it's (bleep) up.
You're-- How old are you?
You're supposed to be...
You're a mother.
And you kicked
a 22nd-year-old...
in their vagina?
22-year-old.
22-- 22nd.
Oh, (bleep), whatever.
22, same (bleep).
Yeah.
22, 22nd, I feel like
it's the same thing.
Hey, Janelle,
like I'mand hate me,nywhere.ñd
but if I ever get
I'm gonna be s
're gonna be out.
You've had problems with me
since day one.
And if your ex is really
about you,
let's see
if he's ■■■■
■■ou're ou this house.really
about you,
Before her ex came in here,
she was painting
this perfect picture.
Mm-hmm.
Like, wait till my ex
come in here.
I'ma show y'all.
BuP speaking.
How (bleep)...
I would love for you
to do that again.
D■■■■■■■p■p■p■p■p■p■p■p■p■■
(woman)
Oh, my God!
What relationships
are gonna get
messed up today?
Ahh!
Please not me.
I'ma say Morgan.
I'm feeling it.
Don't wield that (bleep).
Chad has not been
to the beach yet.
(Morgan)
It has to be Chad.
♪♪
(Nicole)
(bleep)!
(cheering)
Oh, my tits look so good!
(bleep)!
(bleep).
So who's the last person?
Please not me.
Please.
(bleep)!
(cheering)
(overlapping chatter)
Why?
Aw, damn it.
Oh, my God.
Just give me a little bit
of time before
another one comes.
Can I just enjoy my peace?
Bring up some men.
Bye, girls.
Bye.
Bye, Morgan.
d.
Good luck.
♪♪
(Morgan)  I have sos
in this house.
Like, Corey needs to go home.
So I am worried.
I feel like I have finally
gotten to a good place with Jay,
and I just-- I don't want an ex
to come and screw that up.
Best-case scenario is that
it's somebody else's ex,
not mine,
and I can just go back
in the house and have fun
with Chad,
and not have anybody try
interrupting my little
honeymoon.
How y'all feeling?
Terrible.
I'm clueless.
(Romeo)
You're clueless?
For sure.
I don't need
a third, Romeo.
I think me and Jay are
on good terms finally.
So Corey's not
confusing things for you?
Um, I just don't think
it's gonna work between
me and him.
Nicole, how are things
with you and Chad?
We're good.
I feel like you're gonna
(bleep) it up though,
so bring on the exes.
(Romeo)
By the end of this
whole experience,
some of you may find new love,
rekindle with an old love,
or just say (bleep) love.
But the real question:
Are you completely over your ex?
It's time.
No.
Let's bring 'em out.
(bleep).
My ex coming in?
Like, he doesn't need
to be here.
Just throw him back
in the water.
It's like, how much more
can I take?
I haven't cracked yet,
but I feel like if an ex
comes out of the water,
I might reach my cracking point.
♪♪
♪ Fun, everybody love a bomber,
balls are great... ♪
Oh, that's not my ex!
Yeah, that's not mine either.
♪ Go ahead,
treat yourself... ♪♪
My name is Monte,
from Memphis, Tennessee,
and you may know me from
"Big Brother: Over the Top."
Being a southern gentleman is
about treating a girl right.
Opening the door for her,
not cussing, acting a fool
in front of her,
but also smacking her ass
as she walks through the door.
Me and Morgan met
in the Big Brother house.
We dated for six months
and then she decided
she wants to move to L.A.,
so that kind of put a,
you know, rut in the groove.
I'm here to not only
rekindle me and Morgan,
but I know for a fact
that Morgan is the one
I wanna settle down with.
And I'm at that point in my life
where I'm ready.
What's up, man?
Doing good.
What's going on, Monte?
How do you like
seeing Morgan over there?
She looks pretty good, man.
Stop.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Why you here?
Gotta get her back, man.
Get her back?
Yeah.
He's trying to get you back!
Great opportunity
to take her back.
7/It is,
■ulifetime.
Ugh!
What happened between
y'all two?
I ended up moving
to Los Angeles.
It was too much
of long distance
got in the way and--
So you left him hanging?
It was too hard being
so far apart.
Seeing Monte brings back
a lot of good memories.
We don't really have
any fights.
You real flustered
right now, like--
Yeah, I'm flustered
because I'm already living
with two exes,
and now you'retoss.
But this connection
seem genuineere.
Even from the other ones,
I'm feeling something.
I think there is
a genuine connection,
but it's difficult
because I got some issues
back at the house.
Don't play with Jay's feelings.
I think that this is something
between Jay and Morgan
that can potentially ruin them.
We got some things
to figure out.
I'm done.
(bleep), (bleep)!
No, Morgan!
(bleep)!
(sobbing)
I dream of reaching
my highest peak.
I dream of expressing my
inner-most passionq.
I dream of robots that improve
quality of life for humans.
Umm, I dream of getting my
Taco Bell delivered.
Like, to my house.
My dreams are unstoppa
Unstoppable.
My dreams are my fire.
My dreams are much more
simple. And taco related.
Am I in the right commercial?
You gotta get out there!
No one is going to
hand it to you.
That's what I'm saying.
I'd rather stay in and have Taco
Bell literally handed to me.
Bring on the nay-sayers.
Bring on the oS
Tacos, the Crunch Wraps, a
Chalupa.
I don't know the meaning of
failure.
I don't know how to quit!
I don't know what's going on!
Woah! We're doing it guys.
Achieving our dreams.
Hey.
Thank you!
No problem.
Introducing Taco Bell
delivery.
Delievered by GrubHub.
It's your taco dreams
delivered.
You're a real inspiration,
man.
This guy gets it.
♪♪
Your toothpaste may taste fresh,
but is it removing
enough harmful plaque
that can lead to
tooth decay and gum disease?
Try Arm & Hammer Complete Care.
Only Arm & Hammer contains
50% natural baking soda
which neutralizes acid to
protect enamel.
The foaming formula
penetrates hard to reach areas
to help disrupt plaque build up.
And is proven to remove
up to 5X more plaque
than a regular toothpaste.
For a deep cleaning toothpaste
you can actually feel working,
Try Arm & Hammer Complete Care.
This has been Medifacts
for Arm & Hammer.
[ screams ]
Ah!
Oh great, you're up.
No way.
I just got
Ahhh!
♪ ♪
Huh, só■
This time it's different.
The killer is coming
after all of us.
Oh! Whatever.
Ah!
Bye.
[ screams ]
Who are you?
Hey! It's me! Your dry skin!
I'm craving something
we're missing.
The ceramides in CeraVe.
They help restore
my natural barrier,
so I can lock in moisture...
and keep us protected.
We've got to have
each other's backs...
and fronts.
CeraVe. What your skin CraVes.
♪♪
So how you been?
I've been good.
It's been an experience,
to say the least.
Um, I'll go ahead
and fill you in since Romeo
told me I need to be honest.
Yeah, shoot me straight.
Don't lie to me.
I feel like I'm
an emotional wreck at all times
in this house.
It's like I'm the only person
with three exes.
Some people don't even have one
ex and I'm dealing with th
Like, I need to get Corey out
of this house, and he's honestly
pretty boring.
Jay came in the house.
I kind of rekindled things
with him.
Then Corey came in,
so it was kind of like...
Double whammy.
...a weird messy
love triangle.
But I thought I had it
figured out till you
walked up on the beach.
Me and Monte had a great
relationship before this.
It didn't end badly.
My family loves him.
He's unfortunately the exact
kind of guy that my dad
would want me to marry,
which is terrifying.
You're my girl.
Everything happens
for a reason.
So I really think,
you know,
Jay might be cool,
but, you know,
you gotta remember back
to what we had too.
We could rekindle that
even better.
I don't know who this
Jay guy is, but, uh,
he's gonna have to run
for his money, 'cause,
uh, Monte's coming.
Give me a fair shot.
That's all I ask.
Okay.
And I promise you,
you'll reconsider.
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ It's time to go, go,
go, whoa ♪
♪ It's time to go, go, go,
let's go ♪
♪ It's time to go,
go, go, whoa ♪
♪ Do you wanna,
do you wanna go? ♪♪
How you feeling though
this morning?
I'm cool.
Like, the only thing I was
actually, like, I was thinking
about, like, last night, was,
like, no one ever pulled her
to the side and was like,
"Yo, I understand you're upset,
but, like, how you're reacting,
like, that's not okay."
Depending on how Janelle
comes back from the hotel,
I'm hoping to see, uh,
a new-- a new person.
Uh, the girl that I
used to know.
Here we go.
Oh, (bleep)!
Oh, Nicole! Sha!
Chad, you're safe!
So Nicole is back now
and she doesn't have an ex,
and I'm just like,
"Thank God I don't have to deal
with that situation."
So how did the guy look?
Tell me.
Does he look cute
or whatever?
I'm kind of scared
for Jay.
(Janelle)
Why?
He said he's here
to get her back,
and he's here for no other
reason but to get her back.
(Chad)
Oh, (bleep).
Honestly, it should be called
"Morgan's Ex on the Beach."
Like, how many exes
do you have, girl?
Like, just stop.
(cheering)
(all exclaiming)
All right, pull the chair,
pull the chair, pull the chair.
Hold on.
Hey, Morgan.
Take a seat.
Let the man
do the talking.
Goddamn.
(laughter)
This Monte character?
(grunts) Damn!
Ugh!
Um, I will say this.
All the boys you
brought into the house
are fine as (bleep).
And-- yes.
So at least
I have good taste.
What are you here for?
What are your intentions?
What are my intentions?
Are you here to h her?
e ■;  to rekindle that ?
Hell yeah, man.
I'm gonna rekindle the fire.
What are you talking about?
Okay, there we go.
"Oh, I'm gonna be just Mr. Tough
Guy here to steal your girl.
"I'ma flirt with her in front
of you and I'm gonna pretend
like I'm not.
Ha ha! I'm so cool!"
Clown.
If things don't work out
with Jay,
are we allowed to take him
into our relationship?
y
(laughter)
You're allowed to take him
right now if you want.
We can share.
(announcer)
Oh, God, it's so sweet
it's making me sick.
Let's see if everyone else
can be so levelheaded
as Janelle, Farrah, and Nurys
return from their stay
at the hotel.
Baby, baby, baby!
Hey!
elle.
Whoo!
What's up?
So I've had a night
to cool down, relax.
Going in the house, for me,
it is stressful
because I'm dealing
to with the factlax.
that I really am, like,
heartbroken for real.
Diandra, can I talk to you?
Yes.
My main point
to pull Diandra aside
was to apologize to her
and let her know that, hey,
I know we've had our beefs
in the past.
Like, I know we personally
don't care for each other,
but the attack I made on her
was not personal at all.
So basically I just wanted
to genuinely apologize
for putting my hands on you.
Like, my issues are with him.
Like, I should conduct myself
better just as a human being.
You (bleep) kiss her?!
You're gonna kiss her?!
That is her ex.
Oh, (bleep).
Oh, you ain't tell me that.
(bleep) you laughing,
bitch?!
Janelle! Janelle! Janelle!
You (bleep)hole!
So I apologize.
I accept your apology.
Um, I wasn't
laughing at you.
Like, I'm sorry.
Like, when I get nervous,
I'm like...
(nervous chuckle)
But I literally--
all I said, I looked back,
like, this is crazy.
And thankful that you came
to apologize for putting
your hands on me.
No problem.
Like, I meant it, 'cause I
shouldn't be hitting people.
I saw Janelle go up to Diandra,
apologize for the whole thing,
argument they had,
and just literally broke down.
And you know what?
It takes a grown person
to apologize and to admit that.
I accept your apology.
With me, if someone says sorry
and they genuinely mean it,
I will forgive you.
Will I forget?
No. I'm not stupid.
I will definitely keep
my eyes up open,
but the minute you say sorry,
all right, cte.
I'ma do a handshake.
Okay.
We'll take it slow.
Yes.
Okay. Okay, thank you.
All right.
(announcer)
Now that Janelle and Diandra are
on the same page,
the house vibes seem to be
in a good place.
Maybe Farrah and Nurys
can squash their beef too.
Hello, house.
Hey, Farrah.
Hello.
There's another one.
So I'm back today
and I'm going in the house
and I'm just staying away
from literally everything,
everyone, and (bleep) them.
Aww.
Have a drink.
I'm back.
(screaming)
(laughter)
I'm extremely happy
that Nurys came back here.
She did nothing wrong,
but I understand as to why
she had to leave.
But I am genuinely upset
that Farrah is still here.
I'm gonna go ahead and leave it
in the fate of the Lord
and He will take care of that.
Karma's a bitch.
(indistinct chatter)
Good.
So if I started talking
to another girl,
she'd probd out.
Hey, can we talk?
Hi, how are you?
Sure.
In private?
Okay.
I don't have
to (bleep) apologize
because I reacted like
a normal human being,
but better than a normal
human being,
'cause a normal human being
wouldn't have stopped
(bleep) hitting her.
(announcer)
Actually, a normal human being
probably wouldn't kick someone
in the vagina.
I guess I just wanted
to ask where your head
was at yesterday.
'Cause I'm confused
as to where all that
animosity came from.
All that, like--
Okay, so I'm
not confused.
I'm very aware about
what happened yesterday.
When I come in
to just hear what
my friend's ex-boyfriend
is saying,
all I'm hearing is insults,
um, from you about me,
acting like you know me.
I think--
That all was brought up
afterwards, so that's not
what we're talking about.
And continuation of that
and that was--
No, see, now you're
trying to play victim.
That's not what
we're gonna do.
So I'm not a victim.
So I know you
were just drinking.
I'm not drinking.
Okay. Okay.
I'm wide awake.
I have no patience for that.
I apologized for you
insulting me, you touching me.
No.
See, that's that--
no, no.
And I'm the bigger woman.
Okay. Ha, okay.
So I'm a real woman who knows
what really happened.
Okay, okay.
You're out of control.
Oh, my God.
She's literally
delusional.
So stop.
Get in control.
This bitch is delusional, yo.
Okay!
except for herself and■d@■d@■d■d
anybody in this house
@■dYou're so embarras■d
@■d■d■d w■d■d■d  for trash like.
This bitch is delusional, yo.
Okay!
(Nurys)
Bitch, you're the trash.
You kicked me in the vagina
because I was having
a conversation
with someone.
Like, (bleep) psychotic.
Get ahold of yourself,
out-of-control groupie.
What's wrong?
No, she's still lying
and is a trash can.
■■I know I'm a bigger person.
She's a whore.
Do I need to apologize
to someone
who put that on themselves,
who caused that for themselves,
who (bleep) deserves worse
than what she got?
No.
Now, eyeliner goes NYC-proof.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil
from Maybelline New York.
Smudge resistant.
Sweat resistant.
Waterproof.
Up to 36-hour wear
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil.
Only from Maybelline New York.
)
You see Brad,
songs are really about
big life moments.
Baby shower here.
Big. Life. Moment.
What is in here? Ohh!
Oh, I hope it's
a life insurance policy.AC
What?
It's a sensible gift.
Protection for you
and your family,
Nationwide has all the tools
to help you find
the right coverage.
Tiny baby shoes.
So close.
(Peyton)
Makes no sense.
Babies can't even walk.
Should havlife insurance policy.
Makes no sense.
Plus it would have been
a great song.
Think about it,
the lyrics,
the beneficiaries...
Brad, where are you going?
oR
This bitch
is delusional, yo.
It's (bleep) delusional.
Trash can!
Trash?
Have you seen the way
that you carry yourself?
Wow, like, what are you--
What the (bleep)?
Trash can outside
is a liar.
Now, you don't kick nobody in
the vagina, point blank, period.
Save vaginas!
(announcer) Nur  for .
You know what would solve
all these problems?
A nice family dinner
just like mom used to make.
Okay, so who knows
how to call for delivery?
(laughter)
Domino's!
No, seriously.
I'm obviously a peacemaker.
And I feel like maybe
all the exes cooking dinner
for the OGs tonight could help
the entire house, really.
Are we making
some bad (bleep)?
No, we're trying
to keep the peac   All right.
So I am taking control
of the situation.
(Rob)
Okay, let's do this.
We need to boil
the sweet potatoes.
Yeah, I got you.
Okay.
I'm gonna handle
the meat...
like I usually do.
(laughter)
I'm gonna get you a pot
and then I think
we put it back in there.
We're doing some tacos,
burritos,
a couple loaves of bread,
a bacon and Brussels sprout
salad...
That ain't good.
It's gonna be good,
trust me.
...and basically anything
we can find in the fridge.
This is looking
so beautiful, guys.
I'm so proud of us.
Dinner is served!
Yay! Dinnertime!
You guys made that?
All right, where's
the PB&J platter at?
This mother(bleep) wants
a PB&J.
(bleep) like
catered food.
(overlapping chatter, cheering)
I think this is the last supper
before the storm.
(all)
Yes.
So, Jesus, take it away.
Jesus, stand up.
Take the wheel, Jesus!
♪♪
(overlapping shouting)
(alarm blaring)
(bleep)!
Oh, my God, here we go.
Chad, you gotta (bleep) read.
"Exes, you can'tnner
without dessert."
I knew it!
Oh!
Some (bleep) about to pop off,
man, I can just smell it.
"Head down to the Shack
of Secrets to satisfy
your sweet tooth."
Exes?
All of us?
(Chad)
All the exes.
(overlapping chatter)
Welcome to hell!
♪♪
Whoo!
There can't be a bunch
of singles without
getting rid of some of us.
No, this is, like,
gonna be (bleep) up.
I can feel it.
Who got the best hearing?
You two.
Positive vibes.
Positive vibes.u■■
"While you served the singles
dishes, they were busy
serving disses."
Oh...
"Press play to find out."
What's his name?
Nelson does not care
about Nurys.
He said that she was always
the side chick, the one that he
would just hit up to (bleep).
Ooh!
We play the video
and it's all of the OG singles
talking (bleep) about us exes.
Diandra, she's a smart one,
but that's not gonna save you
from all these cuts
you about to get, bitch.
She's a rude
(bleep) bitch.
We didn't order a (bleep)
hooker on demand.
Bitch!
Don't call me a hooker
when you're a po
■
Can I combine
Jay's personality
with Corey's, like, looks?
Morgan, it's you saying Jay's
personality with Corey's looks,
you would combine it.
You're so (bleep).
(laughs)
No, I'm actually so (bleep).
And then I would literally have
my perfect man.
(bleep).
(Jay)
No!
You don't freaking say that!
7■■If youte me and
then you say that, it's like,
hy am I giving you
many chances?"
Because you have treated me like
(bleep) on, like, every level.
And I'm just getting sick of it.
I like
So this is what
you wanted.
Like, what's--
how's that make you feel?
Confused.
I wish you would've
said that from the get-go.
No.
(Morgan grunting)
She told you she
didn't kiss anyone?
(grunts)
"Exes, can the singles have
their cake and eat it too?
Bring it to the table
and serve it up to find out."
Let's do it.
Whoo!
Hey, man.
No, it's all good.
No, no matter
what happens here,
I'm not gonna
bull(bleep) you
about that.
I'll tell straightforward.
I know that.
I feel really bad
for Jay right now.
'Cause I can imagine
being a man hearing that,
saying you're only half
of what I want.
If I was him,
I would almost walk away,
and it's making me contemplate
ind of person
is too.
I've only been here
for two hours and this place
is losing its mind.
I am already starting to see
it looks like a hornet's
Whoo!
Dessert time, people!
So they bring up
this big pink cake,
and I'm like, "Thank you?"
We just heard a lot of people
like to have their cake...
And eat it too.
...and eat it too, people.
(bleep) that.
The exes already have a face on,
and y'all just came from
the Shack of Secrets
and y'all looking at us like
y'all just seen a dead ghost.
Downstairs we saw
every conversation
anybody ever talked (bleep)
about us.
Jay's face looks like
he just saw, like,
a million dead puppies.
I see something in his eyes
I've never seen before.
Farrah, you said that you didn't
know that they hired a hooker,
calling me a hooker.
Are you (bleep)--
I haven't said anything
different when I was
yelling yesterday.
No, honey,
I am not a hooker.
But you're a porn star!
How can you even have
your opinion?
I am not a hooker.
The next person
that calls me--
Do not call me a hooker,
because you do not know me...
(bleep)!
...because you were the one
masturbating on a video!
(bleep) you.
Okay?
That's all I can say
about that.
If a ex pop out,
I (bleep).
■■
WaiThat's whats a bottle.C
I think it is.
Ohh...
Pretty sure that's a bottle.
Girl, get--
get irty, honey.
Oh, (bleep), (bleep), (bleep).
(indistinct chatter)
(bleep).
Wow!
(all exclaiming)
So we got another message,
and I'm thinking like,
pssh, ain't nothing good
gonna come out of this.
We haven't had no good news yet
in that damn bottle, man.
"And now for the icing
on the cake.
"Because revenge
is a dish best served cold,
"it's time to flip the script.
Exes, you now have
the power."
(cheers and applause)
That's some (bleep).
Nice!
We find out that the exes
are going to get the power
to send one single home.
And I'm thinking...
oh, (bleep)!
Tables have turned, bitches,
and I'm here to come for each
and every one of you.
♪♪
L'OREAL PARIS INTRODUCES
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
LESS TEXTURE
MORE COLOR
LESS EXCESS
MORE IMPÑ■■■■
ALL DAY MATTE
BARE LIP SENSATION
ROUGE SIGNATURE
MATTE COLORED INK
BY L'OREAL PARIS
WE'RE WORTH IT
♪♪
When I see Obstacles,
I create opportunities.
When I see adversity,
I find a way.
When I hear never,
I say now.
Southern New Hampshire
University is education
made to fit your goals.
With over 200 rograms,
flexible class schedules
and some of the lowest online
tuition rates in the nation.
So, when I face barriers,
I can break through.
Break through at SNHU.edu.
Hello, there.
Do we go crunchy-cool
or golden Classic?
I know.
One for me and
one for you.
Now that's a sandwich!
Lay's.
Make Life Flavorful.
■/c/C/■■■/■@■@■@e@■■■■■■■■
♪♪
(announcer)
Welcome back.
(cheers and applause)
ncer)
Now that the exes have
the power,
one of you (bleep)-talking
singles is going home.
About time!
So I'm confused what the (bleep)
is happening here,
but you gotta let me know.
I mean, you just (bleep) up
my whole damn dinner.
Spicy!
(Morgan)
Jay? Jay?
(bleep) has hit the fan
and I've been trying
to make it work with Jay.
And I'm like, at this point,
I don't think I'm gonna be able
to dig myself out of this one.
(whispering indiinctly)
I'm done.
(bleep) (bleep) no.
No, no, no, Morgan.
No, I'm done.
Morgan!
(all exclaim)
Oh, (bleep)!
No, like, I'm done, no, like--
Morgan, Morgan.
I'm literally done.
No, I'm done.
I mean, Morgan, my girl,
I don'tMay the Force bee done
karma-wwith you, dear.ess you.
(announcer)
In a living room far, far away,
the exes lean into the dark side
as they strategize
which single
they should get revenge on.
I know you're
gonna say Farrah,
but you gotta look at it
from this point of view.
Yeah, she causes
a lot of (bleep),
but y'all let her.
Like, y'all let-- listen.
Y'all let her words
actually eat up.
Y'all, y'all take,
like-- y'all act like
her words matter.
You only got here yesterday.
That's what I'm saying.
Mm-hmm.
You haven't seen
the whole thing about her.
She is nasty
as a human being.
Nasty.
I haven't really got an
opportunity to talk to Darian.
He was hanging around
Malcolm a lot,
and everyone knows that Malcolm
comes with Diandra and Nurys.
You're not making it easy for me
to forgive you,
because I'm continuously
watching you around people
that I don't like.
♪♪
(sobbing)
I just don't think it's fair!
Morgan, you are much stronger
than this, babe.
Come on!
Okay.
You know what?
I said this whole entire time
I was not gonna reach
my breaking point.
And congratulations,
"Ex on the Beach."
You officially broke me.
What else can I do
to screw up?
I feel like
I screw up everything!
No.
No, you don't.
Just let her cry.
She just needs to cry,
honestly.
Let it out.
I think right now Morgan
actually feels
genuinely sorry and bad.
She hurt Jay's feelings,
and I think Jay has every reason
to feel the way he does.
♪♪
■@■■■■■■■ñ■x(bleep)!
(sustained bleep echoing)
Want to try out my time
It runs on Dor[dog■ ■
Yes!
[humming, thumping]
THIS IS THE GREATEST MOMENT
OF MY LIFE!
GET OUT OF MY YARD!
[birds chirping] Jimmy?
You're so old.
[Crunch!]
How do we tell people they get
the best of both worlds
with Sprint?
How 'bout we get two-sport
legend, Bo Jackson...
...playing a keytar...
■■      ...and a bird-horse.
Woah.Bo>■=ó■
Why don't you just tell
■■Sprint can save themhorse.
more than $1,000
On an LTE Advanced Network
that's now up to 2x faster
than before.
Bo does know.
This is the best robot analogy
I've ever been in.
With a great network and savings
over Verizon and AT&T,
you get the best of both worlds
with Sprint.
Yee-haw!
New Cinnamon Toast Crunch
Churros.
Perfect for breakfast time,
snack time, and night time.
Introducing New Cinnamon Toast
Crunch Churros.■
Churros for breakfast or
whenever.
Mascara in a snap.
New Snapscara from
Maybelline New York.
Smooth, clump-free volume.
Pure pigment formula means...
it's on & off in a snap!
No raccoon eyes.
Smooth, clump-free volume.
New Snapscara!
Only from Maybelline New York.
I'll take a Coke.
Is Pepsi Ok?
Is Pepsi, OK?
Is Pepsi, OK!?
[laughter]
Are puppies, OK?
Is a sstar, OK?
Is the laughter of
a small child, OK?
Pepsi's more than, OK!
It's
Okayyyy
Okurrrr
♪ I Like It ♪ñ
rat have
we learned today?
You want a Pepsi?
I want a Pepsi.
There you go.
Okurrr. Aaahh.
I've got to come up with
my own catch phrase.
Okayyy
(announcer)
Welcome back.
Before the break,
the exes found out
that they all had power
for tomorrow's elimination,
which is bad news for some
of our misbehaved singles.
(Morgan)
You know, I tried so hard
■in this house
totive and happy.
'Cause the last thing
I wanted to do
was come in this house
and lose myself.
And now I feel so lost.
I know I don't have a say
with the exes,
but I want Corey out
before Farrah.
To me, he doesn't
contribute anything.
He has the personality
of a (bleep) pet rock.
And I feel like
Jay's pissed with you
just because, like--
Why would he be pissed
with me?
I feel like he's pissed
at you and her because--
Not at me.
She was kissing back.
It wasn't like a--
she said it was a snipe.
It wasn't a snipe.
It wasn't a snipe at all.
When you're in this house,
you kind of know
that everything is gon reveal.
Morgan's mind, if she gets
evervo
that evI mean, yeah,on reveal.
she could focus on Jay.
But honestly, like,
what's she gonna look at?
You know what I'm saying?
It's hard for me
to deal with the house
and all this
and me and you haven't
gotten anything,
like, resolved.
Resolved.
That (bleep) pisses me off
'cause it's like
I'm over here dying inside.
Darian knows that I do not allow
a man to not be accountable
for his wrongdoings and promise
that he's not gonna do it again.
Like, I need you to repent
to me like I'm Jesus.
When are you gonna fight
for me here
instead of involving yourself
in (bleep) that don't
(bleep) matter?
When the (bleep)
are you gonna fight for me?
You don't even know
what you want.
When we originally broke up,
she left me, literally.
But now I feel like she kind of
wants the best of both worlds.
The onlyhat matters
is me
and if you can't strictly talkf
about me and you right now,lds.
then I will just go to bed.
That's fine.
Okay. Good-bye.
Like, this is (bleep).
That (bleep) again, man.
Let it go.
Are you good with us being done,
yes or no?
Of course not, Janelle.
I feel like we're still
up in the air.
It could go left,
it could go right.
Yeah, we'll see, you know?
It's elimination.
■■
At the end of the day,
I'm my own man.
I'm gonna make my own decisions.
One light ♪
♪nd rair head up
to the sky ♪
Aye-aye-aye-aye ♪♪
We good now?
That is so cute.
(Farrah)
Look at you
and your cute breakfast.
■■
So you haven't got sausage
in a while, so open up.Q
(both laughing)
(Sha)
That was a good one, huh?
Mmm.
Pretty good, huh?
It's tricky.
I really love it.
I'm just gonna go eat up
all my sausage.
See you later.
We both haven't got sausage
in a long time.
(Chad groans)
You know when you're
hung over
and you get ready
and you don't even
remember getting ready
but you just kind of come to
as you're looking good
and you're like, "Yeah"?
Yeah.
It's nice.
♪♪
(Farrah) Murray?
What's up?
I am campaigning.
If I stay...
Mm-hmm.
...then you get something.
I made a "keep Farrah"
campaign book!
And I have my speech ready
for elimination tonigh
I made a "keep Farrah"
campaign book!
Pretend I'm Romeo.
Romeo, this is
my "keep Farrah" campaign.
Okay?
'Kay.
And if I stay,
this is what
the house will get
because I am staying.
I pledge to throw
a yacht party for Jozea.
Okay.
A live-in maid.
Yes.
Jacuzzi cleaner,
bubblier,
and more mimosas
for Chad and Nicole.
Whoo!
Look, I care about
my housemates.
■
Well, and if you just
voted me out,
then that's okay,
I'm on strike.
And I am ready
with my pantsuit and all.
What's up, gangsta?
What's going on?
Talk to me.
I'm just, like,
drained emotionally.
I just didn't wanna get
to that point yesterday
and I did,
and now I feel like
I, like, can't be myself.
What do you want
with us?
t know.
You don't trust me anymore.
It's like--
You honestly believe
that I don't trust you
at all?
I don't know.
(sighs)
I just wish you were
more honest with me.
I would prefer the truth.
Not 10%, 50%, 90%.
Give me the whole
damn thing.
Just wanna say sorry.
I didn't wanna put you
through all this.
■■■Do I still want affection
and touch her all the time
and hug her and (bleep)?
Hell yeah.
So I'll give her a shot.
I'll give her a chance again.
But...
I still care about you.
It's like, are you happier
with me here?
Yeah, what are they gonna do?
Send me a new blond?
(announcer)
We know where Jay stands,
but the rest of the exes
are still making up their minds.
I just wanna know where--
what-- like, where your
heads are at
and why you would--
you know, like,
who you guys wanna vote out
and, like, why?
(Diandra)
The only singles on the chopping
block are Corey and Farrah.
Corey because Morgan
wants him out.
She doesn't feel that she can
continue her relationship
ay while he's here.
And Farrah is
on the chopping block.
It's 'cause she kicked my girl
in the vagina and she needs
to (bleep) off.
Morgan's like,
"Someone help me, please."
But she's not actually
physically getting attacked,
and it's bull(bleep).
You know I get your side,
and I feel so bad for Morgan
that she's gotten bull(bleep)
after bull(bleep)
after bull(bleep).
But to be honest,
she did not get
this physically attacked.
That's so (bleep) up that any
of you guys are even deciding
for even the slightest
(bleep) bit.
Seriously?
I don't understand why people
wanna get Corey out.
Corey hasn't done anything.
Farrcrazy,
sional bitch.
She's the one
that's the problem.
We're supposed to be exesng
and we're supposed
to stick together, correct?
Correct, and none
of you guys had my back.
That's the biggest
bull(bleep) ever.
Even though I know
she hurt you,
and, like, Farrah did
do things wrong,
everyone's done
a couple things wrong,
and at this point, like,
it's like we're not all
gonna come to one.
I think we should all just vote
what we think at this point.
So I'm just gonna go ahead
and crush Farrah just because
I feel like Farrah,
ifgonna respect her,
she'll respect you right back.
She treats all of us pretty good
other than the people
that she doesn't like,
which is everyone
for the most part.
I shouldn't have to (bleep)--
this should be easy.
It shouldn't
even be a question.
I totally understand why
you want her out.
I wish y'all would just
talk it out.
But you don't even
wanna talk to me, so...
I thought she did try
to talk to her.
She did try
to talk to Farrah,
and Farrah just blew--
I already know
I'm the bigger person.
I don't need to.
I'm not going up
to the bitch again.
And yes, I will
call her a bitch
'cause she's a bitch.
Like, I really don't care.
(Nurys)
It sucks to see that people
don't have my back.
I haven't done anything
to deserve that.
(sobbing)
(Nora)
Before we start - how much is my
tax prep going to cost?
(Tax Guy)
I can't really say that until
the end.
(Lisa) [off-screen]
Wait, no.
H&R Block has upfront,
transparent pricing
so you know the price
before you begin.
(Nora)
So, it can work like that.
(Lisa)
Yup!
(Tax Guy)
Oh, so you want transparency.
Oh, um I could give you a
ballpark...
Ummm, hmmmm.
(Lisa)
That's not a price.
(Lisa VO) ♪
Know the price before you begin.
With new upfront transparent
pricing at H&R Block.
In-person or online.
Block has your back.
You can't put a price on love.
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
This is Game Fuel.
It's domination in a can.
b÷b÷b÷b÷b÷b÷b÷b÷b÷b÷b÷b÷b÷b÷b÷b÷
Ahh.
Taste like loser tears.
New Mountain Dew Amp Game Fuel.
Victory In A Can.
C'mon, you Old El Paso Tortilla
Bowls.
Use those flat bottoms.
Onions, tomatoes, don't forget
the cheese.
Let's go ladies.
Those shells aren't going to
lift themselves.
Woooo!
I feel like a new taco.
Anything goes in Old El Paso.
Uh-oh!
Guess what day it is?
Guess what day it is!
Huh...anybody?
Julie!
Hey...guess what day?
Ah come on, I know
you can hear me.
Mike Mike Mike
Mike Mike...
what day is it Mike?
Ha ha ha ha!
Leslie, guess
what today is?
It's Hump Day.
Whoot Whoot!
Ronny, how happy are folks
who save hundred of dollars
switching to GEICO?
I'd say happier than
a camel on Wednesday.
HUMP DAY!!!
Get happy. Get GEICO.
Fifteen minutes could save
you fifteen percent or more.
Get happy. Get GEICO.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Voluptuous Volume.
Intense Length.
Feathery-Soft Lashes.
This is what
paradise looks like.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Take your lashes to paradise.
■/Ñ■
♪♪
Today is the day that the exes
finally have the power.
Now the singa taste
of their own medicine.
One of you mother(bleep)
is going home.
You're gone, bitch.
Well, I'm just gonna go ahead
and crush Farrah
just because I'm cool with her
and I'm just gonna go ahead
and not even deal
with the whole Corey thing
■      withad blood
ct him.(sighs)
♪♪
Tonight, I am cutting Corey
because I think
that he came here
with a mission to stir up
feelings with Morgan.
I think that's
kind of passed, so...
♪♪
(Corey)
Honestly, I think that people
are, like, trying
to protect Morgan,
but she's, like, you know,
a little bitter at this point,
I think, and she, like, wants
to get me out now.
(Farrah)
I'm shocked that I would even be
up to be eliminated, really.
But as I am,
I'm ready to defend myself.
I'm here to stay.
What up?
What up, everybody?
Looking good.
(applause)
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■)
Now, before we get started,
I want to say something.
■■ííTóTí
There's any more confrontations
that get physical,a
you will be sent home.
We're all about love
here, baby.
All right, let's get down
to business.
Singles, we're gon' do things
a little bit differently
tonight.
Earlier today, the exes voted
for which single they wanted
to crush or cut.
■2■2■2■2■2■■■
ngle tived
the most cut
■
Crush votes, like y'all know,
cancels out cut votes.
And if the vote
results in a tie,
the power will revert
to the remaining singles.
Somemay find new■   rekindle w,
or just say (bleep) love.
By the end of your time here,
we're gonna put you through
the ultimate test.
I've tried real hard to campaign
to get Corey out of this house.
Be able to ans!■&■&■&S■&&
Before we get to these votes,
banybody wanna say anything?
I would like to make a speech.
Wow. Okay.
(Romeospeech.
(Farrah)
Yeah.
So it's a "keep Farrah"
campaign.
But does she forget
we already voted?
If I, Farrah,
am here to stay,
I pledge unlimited
grocery shopping,
live-in maid.
Also lots more toilet paper,
cleaner, and air spray.
We gotta wrap it up
in a second.
Okay, all right.
All who voted for me
to be eliminated
will be on trash duty
and be shunned.
■■■a##■A■■■■
(laughter)
Honestly, in my heart of hearts,
I don't want either Farrah
or Corey to go.
Farrah, we gotta take
a seat right there.
Thank you.
All right.
(cheers and applause)
Whoo!
Thank you.
(giggling)
So funny.
All right, all right,
we gon' get back to it.
Let's get started.
Jozea.
You already know what it is.
You good.
Nothing's in there.
No cut or no crush.
Yes.
You are safe, Jozea.
Maya, Malcolm,
Nicole, Cheyenne, Chad...
you don't have nothing
in your pineapple.
(applause)
Which means you are safe.
We still got a lot of chips
still out there.
♪♪
With that being said,
Morgan,
please step up
to your pineapple.
♪♪
So how would you like
the vo tonight?
I honestly would like Corey
to go home.
It's nothing against him,
but I have three exes
in the house.
Three is enough.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
You got a chip.
But it's a crush.
Duh.    (appla
Have a seat.
So, Janelle,
Mm-hmm.
you've Why don't you step up
of■    to your pineapple?
Sure thing.
See how this goes.
♪♪
(laughter)
Think you have
anything i
)
Maybe.
You never know.
Let's get to it.
Hold on.
You got a chip.
But it's a crush.
(applause)
Wow!
I said actions, people.
I said actions.
You got a crush,
which is a sign of love.
(bleep).
■■■[■■
You better crush all this.
You are safe.
Have a seat, Janelle.
Look at smile, man.
I'm just sayiYou see that?
Changes everything.
He's trying
to get his (bleep).
Yeah, he really is.
We finally got a chip.
Thank you.
(Nelson)
Hey, Romeo.
I don't think he's the one
that put that crush vote
in there.
(all exclaiming)
Oh, (bleep).
Oh, (bleep)!
♪♪
♪ You got a side
that wants more space, ♪
♪ 'Cause every day starts
like a race. ♪
♪ You got a side
that loves that style, ♪
♪ But to fit in those shoes
gonna take awhile. ♪
♪ Today life's
got you runnin'. ♪
♪ Tomorrow big things
are comin'. ♪
♪ That's why Nationwide
is on your side. ♪♪
♪♪
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
With all new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas
starting at just $12.99.
Pick your favorite
stuffed pasta
ke our new
Stuffed Ziti Fritta,
with your choice of
sauce and topping...
then try another
delicious combination.
Plus unlimited
salad and breadsticks.
It's all never ending.
Here's to more from
beginning to endless.
All New Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
[thinking]
They made the original, hot?
♪Oohh, hot stuff
all over my nachos♪
♪Driving over potholes♪
♪Walkin■■■,p■ooo■■qóó■■ó■■■
♪Hotter than a pot roast♪
♪Fingers on my hot chips♪
♪Red handed come on man♪
♪Now I'm a need some chopsticks♪
♪I want it that way♪
>8>■   way♪
The Original, now it's hot.
♪♪
When I see Obstacles,
I create opportunities.
When I see adversity,
I find a way.
When I hear never,
I say now.
Southern New Hampshire
University is education
made to fit your goals.
With over 200 degree programs,
flexible class schedules
and some of the lowest online
tuition rates in the nation.
So, when I face barriers,
I can break through.
Break through at SNHU.edu.
■■■0y
Hy-a-luronic Acid.
It's in here.
New from Revitalift:
Derm Intensives
Hyaluronic Acid Serum
With our highest concentration
of Hyaluronic Acid
Visibly plumps skin
and reduces wrinkles.
Bounce back!
New Revitalift Hyaluronic
Acid Serum
From L'Oreal.
Hey, Romeo,
I don't think he's the one
that put that crush vote
in there.
Oh.
I did.
(all exclaiming)
Oh, (bleep).
Wow.
Winning!
So you gave
the crush vote
to Janelle?
Yes, I did.
What I respect about her
I gave you that crush vote.
but respect that,gized
so that ■2■(applause)2#2#2
Darian ain't getting
his (bleep).
I am pissed because Darian was
going to fully take the credit
for that crush, but instead
ting it on someone
that you barely even know,
it's like, put it towards me
to show me that, like,
you care.
Corey, please step up
to your pineapple.
á
If I had to guess,
you got some chips
in there.
Yeah.
Let's get to it.
First chip, cut.
Got another chip...
which is a cut.
You have two cut votes,
which means you're on
the hot seat.
Take a seat.
I might be going home because
of, like, her messiness,
it's jusir to me
that I would have to
potentially go home.
It'd be stupid for them
to kick me out of the house
'cause I never cause drama.
Like, I'm here to date,
you know, maybe find love.
So, next, Farrah.
Please step up
to your pineapple.
You think you have
any crush votes,
any cut votes?
I mean, I hope I have
some crush votes.
All right, you ready
to get to it?
Yeah.
First one.
I'm so over Farrah!
You're giving everybody
a hard time.
You are a (bleep) person
to everybody.
You kicked one
of my closest friends
house in her vagina.
You need to get
the (bleep) out.
♪♪
(announcer)
Next time on
"Ex on the Beach
A single gets sent home,
but which one?
And the bad girl we've been
waiting for joins the house...
Oh, my God.
(announcer)
...and wastes no time
causing drama.
Apparently you
the (bleep)
of the house.
Who said it?