wanna miss
tonight's twisted elimination,
especially if you're a fan
of revenge.
'Bout damn time!
(thunder rumbling)
♪ We represent
our hood tonight ♪
♪ Come on, we represent
our hood for life... ♪♪
(announcer)
Welcome back.
Let's get you caught up.
Morgan and Jay have worked
through their issues,
and are on the up and up.
What's my favorite
color today?
Pink.
Yup.
(announcer)
But Corey seems to be the pain
in their ass that won't go away.
Chad and Nicole's relationship
is moving to the next level,
taking each other's
measurements.
Wow, you (bleep) it up.
I had it.
No, here.
I got it.
I'm gonna measure it for you,
you (bleep) ding-a-ling.
(announcer)
Janelle's still running hot
after attacking Diandra
for kissing her ex Darian.
And Farrah's discovering her
ripped-up posters,
which was payback by Nurys
for being kicked in the cooter.
Oh, my God.
Someone came up here
and (bleep) up my signs.
All right, so that's
the (bleep) you started!
Did she (bleep) do this?
She might have
did it, Farrah.
Okay.
Well, this is the best one.
Did someone
(bleep) up my-- okay.
All right.
Don't attack all of my amazing,
amazing signs...
that my housemates spent
their time on making for me.
Did someone have an idea
to (bleep) bend all my signs?
■    I (bleep) did! I did!
I happily (bleep) did!
I did, I did, I did, I did!
Nurys did!
She kicked me.
She decided to put
her hands on me,
so I grabbed her
"free Farrah" posters
and I ripped them in half.
Stop! No!
You think I give a (bleep)?
No, no, no, no!
Nurys, no!
Diandra, Diandra!
I know!
If you wanna touch my stuff,
your (bleep) gets
a big "(bleep) you"
down the toilet.
Okay, touch my (bleep), bitch.
Touch it, I dare you.
somebody else's
(bleep).
(Nurys)
I did.
You ugly-ass bitch!
Oh, I'm ugly, bitch?
How much plastic surgery
have you had to fix your face
and your body?
I haven't done not one thing
to my body or my face
and I'm (bleep) gorgeous,
so (bleep) my (bleep), bitch.
(Farrah)
You (bleep)
disgusting bitch.
Sure, sure,
I'll take your (bleep).
I'll take your (bleep)
and put it in the toilet.
If she touches my (bleep),
I'm letting you guys know,
I'ma beat this bitch's ass.
Go ahead, Farrah.
Put that (bleep)
in the toilet.
o
Here it goes.
Here it (bleep) goes.
Come on, sis.
Here it goes.
Put that (bleep)
in the toilet.
She (bleep) bent every one.
She (bleep) your ex, sis!
(laughter)
She bent! She bent!
Disrespect me,
disrespect my stuff,
you will not be respected.
And, um, karma's a bitch.
Oh, (bleep)!
She ripped her (bleep).
Here we go. Here it goes.
Here you go.
Farrah's said
she ripped it all up.
If you argue with Farrah,
she will kick you in the vagina
and put your shoes in the toilet
and flush.
That's some pussy-ass (bleep).
I've never done something
so crazy like that.
It's bad enough that Farrah
already kicked me in the vagina.
Now she's grabbing my sneakers
and she flushes them
down the toilet.
I could've touched her makeup
that was there,
or any of her personal
belongings, and I didn't,
because I have some type
of class.
Don't threaten me!
Don't trip me!
Don't (bleep) attack me!
(announcer)
Since fighting is
a big fat no-no,
Janelle, Nurys, and Farrah are
sent to hotels for the night
with a warning.
Talk (bleep),
get hit, bitch.
0 4@@
I'll see you tomorrow
'cause we always
keepin' positive things.
I love you. Mwah!
Love you too.
♪♪
You guys think the, like,
Farrah-Nurys situation
is gonna continue today or--
Oh, yeah, 100%.
She's in a very precarious legal
situation right now.
Don't be coming around
kicking anyone.
But, like, I just got--
like, this is childish.
Okay, but if you got
kicked in the cooter,
what would you (bleep) do?
I'ma kick you back
in the cooter.
Farrah went back,
and then the security
guard was there.
She tripped over his feet
and Farrah fell on her ass.
Well, good thing she's got
those airbags back there.
No, she-- yeah.
Did she bounce?
(laughter)
♪♪
My ex is definitely
coming before yours.
One of 'em.
One of 'em is coming
and it's gonna
(bleep) up everything.
I don't want Chad's ex
coming into this house.
I will literally ruin
this girl's life
if she thinks for one second
that she has
any upper hand on me
when it comes to Chad.
I will rip her to shreds.
We still gotta have--
we're still going
to the sauna.
I know.
That's still a date.
Exes coming in.
■es, exes.
At the end of the day,
we're just these, like, what?
Skin blobs floating around
on this planet
that's going through space
through a round of ball of fire?
Like, and that's life,
and then you die.
You know, eventually.
(announcer)
Thanks for the deep thoughts,
Einstein.
We to that point yet?
Yeah.
We can have sex
really close to people?
We are?
Okay.
Come here, Corey.
We're gonna have sex
on top of you.
You're our first victim.
(Corey)
Those guys are so cute together.
I'm peanut butter and jealous
of their relationship.
I really don't have feelings
for Sh
And Morgan, she's kinda
boo'd up with Jay.
I'm peanut butter and jealous
of their relationship.
You know, hopefully I can findn
and be a cute couple.
(siren wailing)
(woman)
Oh, my God!
What relationships
are gonna get
messed up today?
Ahh!
Please not me.
I'ma say Morgan.
I'm feeling it.
Don't wield that (bleep).
Chad has not been
to the beach yet.
(Morgan)
It has to be Chad.
♪♪
(Nicole)
(bleep)!
(cheering)
Oh, my tits look so good!
(bleep)!
(bleep).
So who's the last person?
Please not me.
Please.
(bleep)!
(cheering)
(overlapping chatter)
Why?
Aw, damn it.
Oh, my God.
Just give me a little bit
of time before
another one comes.
Can I just enjoy my peace?
Bring up some men.
Bye, girls.
Bye.
Bye, Morgan.
■÷
Be good.
Good luck.
♪♪
(Morgan)I have so ms
in this house.
Like, Corey needs to go home.
So I am worried.
I feel like I have finally
gotten to a good place with Jay,
and I just-- I don't want an ex
to come and screw that up.
Best-case scenario is that
it's somebody else's ex,
not mine,
and I can just go back
in the house and have fun
with Chad,
and not have anybody try
interrupting my little
honeymoon.
How y'all feeling?
Terrible.
I'm clueless.
(Romeo)
You're clueless?
For sure.
I don't need
a third, Romeo.
I think me and Jay are
on good terms finally.
So Corey's not
confusing things for you?
Um, I just don't think
it's gonna work between
me and him.
Nicole, how are things
with you and Chad?
We're good.
I feel like you're gonna
(bleep) it up though,
so bring on the exes.
(Romeo)
By the end of this
whole experience,
some of you may find new love,
rekindle with an old love,
or just say (bleep) love.
But the real question:
Are you completely over your ex?
It's time.
No.
Let's bring 'em out.
(bleep).
My ex coming in?
Like, he doesn't need
to be here.
Just throw him back
in the water.
It's like, how much more
can I take?
I haven't cracked yet,
but I feel like if an ex
comes out of the water,
I might reach my cracking point.
♪♪
♪ Fun, everybody love a bomber,
balls are great... ♪
Oh, that's not my ex!
Yeah, that's not mine either.
♪ Go ahead,
treat yourself... ♪♪
My name is Monte,
from Memphis, Tennessee,
and you may know me from
"Big Brother: Over the Top."
Being a southern gentleman is
about treating a girl right.
Opening the door for her,
not cussing, acting a fool
in front of her,
but also smacking her ass
as she walks through the door.
Me and Morgan met
in the Big Brother house.
We dated for six months
and then she decided
she wants to move to L.A.,
so that kind of put a,
you know, rut in the groove.
I'm here to not only
rekindle me and Morgan,
but I know for a fact
that Morgan is the one
I wanna settle down with.
And I'm at that point in my life
where I'm ready.
What's up, man?
Doing good.
What's going on, Monte?
How do you like
seeing Morgan over there?
She looks pretty good, man.
Stop.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Why you here?
Gotta get her back, man.
Get her back?
Yeah.
He's trying to get you back!
Great opportunity
to take her back.
■/
It is, man.
Once in a lifetime.
Ugh!
What happened between
y'all two?
I ended up moving
to Los Angeles.
It was too much
of long distance
got in the way and--
So you left him hanging?
It was too hard being
so far apart.
Seeing Monte brings back
a lot of good memories.
We don't really have
any fights.
You real flustered
right now, like--
Yeah, G  because I'm alreG
with two exes,
You real flusand now you'reGg i.
right now, like--
But this connection
seem genuine right here.
Even from the other ones,
I'm feeling something.
I think there is
a genuine connection,
but it's difficult
because I got some issues
back at the house.
Don't play with Jay's feelings.
I think that this is something
between Jay and Morgan
that can potentially ruin them.
We got some things
to figure out.
I'm done.
(bleep), (bleep)!
No, Morgan!
(bleep)!
(sobbing)
Uh-oh!
Guess what day it is?
Guess what day it is!
Huh...anybody?
Julie!
Ah come on, I know
you can hear me.
Mike Mike Mike
Mike Mike...
what day is it Mike?
Ha ha ha ha!
Leslie, guess
what today is?
It's Hump Day.
Whoot Whoot!
Ronny, how happy are folks
who save hundred of dollars
switching to GEICO?
I'd say happier than
a camel on Wednesday.
HUMP DAY!!!
Get happy. Get GEICO.
Fifteen minutes could save
you fifteen percent or more.
Hy-a-luronic Acid
Hyaluronic acid.
It's the skincare ingredient
that everyone is searching for!
And It's in here.
New from Revitalift:
Derm Intensives Hyaluronic
Acid Serum
With our highest concentration
of Hyaluronic Acid in a serum
Visibly plumps skin in
just one week
bounce back!
And reduces wrinkles for
younger-looking skin.
Powerful results
Validated by a panel
of dermatologists
New Revitalift Derm Intensives
Hyaluronic Acid Serum
From L'Oreal Paris
[SFX]■■■■■WW■W■■é■
We're worth it.
[SFX]
♪
Introducing new
Hershey's Milk Chocolate
e's Pieces
Now in one bar
u's Pieces
♪♪
So how you been?
I've been good.
It's been an experience,
to say the least.
Um, I'll go ahead
and fill you in since Romeo
told me I need to be honest.
Yeah, shoot me straight.
Don't lie to me.
I feel like I'm
an emotional wreck at all times
in this house.
It's like I'm the only person
with three exes.
Some people don't even have one
ex and I'm dealing with three.
Like, I need to get Corey out
of this house, and he's honestly
pretty boring.
Jay came in the house.
I kind of rekindled things
with him.
Then Corey came in,
so it was kind of like...
Double whammy.
...a weird messy
love triangle.
But I thought I had it
figured out till you
walked up on the beach.
Me and Monte had a great
relationship before this.
It didn't end badly.
My family loves him.
He's unfortunately the exact
kind of guy that my dad
would want me to marry,
which is terrifying.
You're my girl.
Everything happens
for a reason.
So I really think,
you know,
Jay might be cool,
but, you know,
you gotta remember back
to what we had too.
We could rekindle that
even better.
I don't know who this
Jay guy is, but, uh,
he's gonna have to run
for his money, 'cause,
uh, Monte's coming.
Give me a fair shot.
That's all I ask.
Okay.
And I promise you,
you'll reconsider.
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ It♪ It's time to go, go,
go, go, whoa ♪
♪ Do you wanna,
do you wanna go? ♪♪
How you feeling though
this morning?
I'm cool.
Like, the only thing I was
actually, like, I was thinking
about, like, last night, was,
like, no one ever pulled her
to the side and was like,
"Yo, I understand you're upset,
but, like, how you're reacting,
like, that's not okay."
Depending on how Janelle
comes back from the hotel,
I'm hoping to see, uh,
a new-- a new person.
Uh, the girl that I
used to know.
Here we go.
Oh, (bleep)!
Oh, Nicole! Sha!
Chad, you're safe!
So Nicole is back now
and she doesn't have an ex,
and I'm just like,
"Thank God I don't have to deal
with that situation."
So how did the guy look?
Tell me.
Does he look cute
or whatever?
I'm kind of scared
for Jay.
(Janelle)
Why?
He said he's here
to get her back,
and he's here for no other
reason but to get her back.
(Chad)
Oh, (bleep).
Honestly, it should be called
"Morgan's Ex on the Beach."
Like, how many exes
do you have, girl?
Like, just stop.
(cheering)
(all exclaiming)
All right, pull the chair,
pull the chair, pull the chair.
Hold on.
Hey, Morgan.
Take a seat.
Let the man
do the talking.
Gah damn.
(laughter)
This Monte character?
(grunts) Damn!
Ugh!
Um, I will say this.
All the boys you
brought into the house
are fine as (bleep).
And-- yes.
So at least
I have good taste.
What are you here for?
What are your intentions?
What are my intentions?
Are you here to be with her?
■÷  Are ■;  to rekindle that fi?
Hell yeah, man.
I'm gonna rekindle the fire.
What are you talking about?
Okay, there we go.
"Oh, I'm gonna be just Mr. Tough
Guy here to steal your girl.
"I'ma flirt with her in front
of you and I'm gonna pretend
like I'm not.
Ha ha! I'm so cool!"
Clown.
If things don't work out
with Jay,
are we allowed to take him
into our relationship?
(laughter)
You're allowed to take him
right now if you want.
We can share.
(announcer)
Oh, God, it's so sweet
it's making me sick.
Let's see if everyone else
can be so levelheaded
as Janelle, Farrah, and Nurys
return from their stay
at the hotel.
Baby, baby, baby!
Hey!
ç■■7■7's Janelle.
Whoo!
What's up?
So I've had a night
to cool down, relax.
Going in the house, for me,
it is stressful
because I'm dealing
with the fact
that I really am, like,
heartbroken for real.
Diandra, can I talk to you?
Yes.
My main point
to pull Diandra aside
was to apologize to her
and let her know that, hey,
I know we've had our beefs
in the past.
Like, I know we personally
don't care for each other,
but the attack I made on her
was not personal at all.
So basically I just wanted
to genuinely apologize
for putting my hands on you.
Like, my issues are with him.
Like, I should conduct myself
better just as a human being.
You (bleep) kiss her?!
You're gonna kiss her?!
That is her ex.
Oh, (bleep).
Oh, you ain't tell me that.
(bleep) you laughing,
bitch?!
Janelle! Janelle! Janelle!
You (bleep)hole!
So I apologize.
I accept your apology.
Um, I wasn't
laughing at you.
Like, I'm sorry.
Like, when I get nervous,
I'm like...
(nervous chuckle)
But I literally--
all I said, I looked back,
like, this is crazy.
And thankful that you came
to apologize for putting
your hands on me.
No problem.
Like, I meant it, but I
shouldn't be hitting people.
I saw Janelle go up to Diandra,
apologize for the whole thing,
argument they had,
and just literally broke down.
And you know what?
It takes a grown person
to apologize and to admit that.
I accept your apology.
With me, if someone says sorry
and they genuinely mean it,
■     I will forgi
With me,Will I forget?ys sorry
and No. I'm not stupid. it,
I will definitely keep
my eyes up open,
but the minute you say sorry,
all right, clean slate.
I'ma do a handshake.
Okay.
We'll take it slow.
Yes.
Okay. Okay, thank you.
All right.
(announcer)
Now that Janelle and Diandra are
on the same page,
the house vibes seem to be
in a good place.
Maybe Farrah and Nurys
can squash their beef too?
Hello, house.
Hey, Farrah.
Hello.
There's another one.
So I'm back today
and I'm going in the house
and I'm just staying away
from literally everything,
everyone, and (bleep) them.
Aww.
Have a drink.
I'm back.
(screaming)
(laughter)
I'm extremely happy
that Nurys came back here.
She did nothing wrong,
but I understand as to why
she had to leave.
But I am genuinely upset
that Farrah is still here.
I'm gonna go ahead and leave it
in the fate of the Lord
and He will take care of that.
Karma's a bitch.
(indistinct chatter)
Good.
So if I started talking
to another girl,
she'd probably find out.
Hey, can we talk?
Hi, how are you?
Sure.
In private?
Okay.
I don't have
to (bleep) apologize
because I reacted like
a normal human being,
but better than a normal
human being,
'cause a normal human being
wouldn't have stopped
(bleep) hitting her.
(announcer)
Actually, a normal human being
probably wouldn't kick someone
in the vagina.
I guess I just wanted
to ask where your head
was at yesterday.
'Cause I'm confused
as to where all that
animosity came from.
All that, like--
Okay, so I'm
not confused.
I'm very aware about
what happened yesterday.
When I come in
to just hear what
my friend's ex-boyfriend
is saying,
all I'm hearing is insults,
um, from you about me,
acting like you know me.
I think--
That all was brought up
afterwards, so that's not
what we're talking about.
And continuation of that
and that was--
No, see, now you're
trying to play victim.
That's not what
we're gonna do.
So I'm not a victim.
So I know you
were just drinking.
I'm not drinking.
Okay. Okay.
I'm wide awake.
I have no patience for that.
I apologized for you
insulting me, you touching me.
No.
See, that's that--
no, no.
And I'm the bigger woman.
Okay. Ha, okay.
So I'm a real woman who knows
what really happened.
Okay, okay.
You're out of control.
Oh, my God.
She's literally
delusional.
So stop.
Get in control.
This bitch is delusional, yo.
Okay!
Farrah does not care abo anye
except for herself and s■■@@@@@.
■d■d■d■d■d■d■d■d■d■d■d■■d■■d■■d.
(Nurys)
Bitch, you're the trash.
You kicked me in the vagina
because I was having
a conversation
with someone.
Like, (bleep) psychotic.
Get ahold of yourself,
out-of-control groupie.
What's wrong?
No, she's still lying
and is a trash can.
I know I'm a bigger person.
She's a whore.
Do I need to apologize
to someone
who put that on themselves,
who caused that for themselves,
who (bleep) deserves worse
than what she got?
No.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Voluptuous Volume.
Intense Length.
Feathery-Soft Lashes.
This is what
paradise looks like.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Take your lashes to paradise.
Hello, there.
Do we go crunchy-cool
or golden Classic?
I know.
One for me and
one for you.
Now that's a sandwich!
Lay's.
Make Life Flavorful.
♪ Seed to the oat, to the O ♪
♪ To the honey in each bite ♪
♪ Healthy hearts make life
sweeter ♪
♪ So you can live it right ♪
♪ The good goes arouaround  andA
It's time for some
Straight Talk.
Hallelujah,
it's tax refund time.
So what are you going to do with
all that glorious extra money?
No, not that!
Here's a better plan.
Try Straight Talk Wireless and
get 25 gigs of high-speed data
for just $45 bucks a month.
That's right, all on America's
best 4G LTE networks.
Plus, save up to 200 dollars on
a Samsung Galaxy S9
with in-store activation.
Straight Talk Wireless.
Everything for less.
■■#    Your skin deserves bette.
Garnier Micellar Cleansing Water
with micelles that
work like a magnet.
It's a pure way to remove
stubborn makeup
without harsh rubbing.
Cleansing, reinvented.
Micellar Water.
By Garnier,
Naturally!
Every year,
Team Rubicon enlists the help
of veterans to provide relief
Every year,
to communities
affected by natural disasters.
Do it for those
who need■á■■
Mountain Dew
is proud
to support
the efforts
of
Team Rubicon.
Let's Do.
Juicy, sizzling steak.
Hand-tossed original dough.
Fresh cut onions,
crunchy green peppers,
a delicious
four cheese blend,
and our creamy Philly sauce.
All on the best
Philly Cheesesteak
you can get on a pizza.
Right now get
the new Philly
or any large specialty
Papa John's pizza
for just 12 bucks.
The iPhone XR is a marvel in
technology.
Yeah.
This edge to edge screen is
unbelievable.
Am I nuts or does everything
look better on an iPhone?
Both.
And with our Unlimited plan,
people can choose the best in
entertainment.
HBO, Cinemax, Showtime...
STARZ, VRV, Amazon Music, or
Pandora...
Now people can get what
they want.
Because everyone's different.
I feel like we shouldn't talk
for a couple of days.
AT&T has the only unlimited plan
that gives you your choice of
top-tier entertainment.
Get an iPhone XR on us when
you buy the latest iPhone.
MORE FOR YOUR THING. THAT'S OUR
THING.
I know it's hard Maddie.
But I promise,
it's gonna get better.
♪ ♪
(mom giggles)
This bitch
is delusional, yo.
It's (bleep) delusional.
Trash can!
Trash?
Have you seen the way
that you carry yourself?
Wow, like, what are you--
What the (bleep)?
Trash can outside
is a liar.
Now, you don't kick nobody in
the vagina, point blank, period.
Save vaginas!
(announcer)
ops to
for at
You know what would solve
all these problems?
A nice family dinner
just like mom used to make.
(overlapping chatter and toasts)
(cheering)
I think this is the last supper
before the storm.
(all)
Yes.
So, Jesus, take it away.
Jesus, stand up.
Take the wheel, Jesus!
♪♪
(overlapping shouting)
(alarm blaring)
(bleep)!
Oh, my God, here we go.
Chad, you gotta (bleep) read.
"Exes, you can't have dinner
without dessert."
I knew it!
Oh!
Some (bleep) about to pop off,
man, I can just smell it.
"Head down to the Shack
of Secrets to satisfy
your sweet tooth."
Exes?
All of us?
(Chad)
All the exes.
(overlapping chatter)
Welcome to hell!
♪♪
Whoo!
There can't be a bunch
of singles without
getting rid of some of us.
No, this is, like,
gonna be (bleep) up.
I can feel it.
Who got the best hearing?
You two.
Tell us.
Positive vibes.
Poibes.
"While you served the singles
dishes, they were busy
serving disses."
Oh...
"Press play to find out."
What's his name?
Nelson does not care
about Nurys.
He said that she was always
the side chick, the one that he
would just hit up to (bleep).
Ooh!
We play the video
and it's all of the OG singles
talking (bleep) about us exes.
Diandra, she's a smart one,
but that's not gonna save you
from all these cuts
you about to get, bitch.
She's a rude
(bleep) bitch.
We didn't order a (bleep)
hooker on demand.
Bitch!
Don't call me a hooker
when you're a porn star.
Can I combine
Jay's personality
with Corey's, like, looks?
Morgan, it's you saying Jay's
personality with Corey's looks,
you would combine it.
You're so (bleep).
(laughs)
No, I'm actually so (bleep).
And then I would literally have
my perfect man.
(bleep).
(Jay)
No!
You don't freaking say that!
If you"Why am I giving you
en y many chances?"'s like
Because you have treated me like
(bleep) on, like, every level.
And I'm just getting sick of it.
I like you.
So this is what
you wanted.
Like, what's--
how's that make you feel?
Confused.
I wish you would've
said that from the get-go.
No.
(Morgan grunting)
She told you she
didn't kiss anyone?
(grunts)
"Exes, can the singles have
their cake and eat it too?
Bring it to the table
and serve it up to find out."
Let's do it.
Whoo!
Hey, man.
No, it's all good.
No, no matter
what happens here,
I'm not gonna
bull(bleep) you
about that.
I'll tell straightforward.
I know that.
I feel really bad
for Jay right now.
'Cause I can imagine
being a man hearing that,
saying you're only half
of what I want.
If I,
and it's making me contemplate
what kind of person
Morgan i
I've only been here
for two hours and this place
is losing its mind.
I am already starting to see
it looks like a hornet's nest.
Whoo!
Dessert time, people!
So they bring up
this big pink cake,
and I'm like, "Thank you?"
We just heard a lot of people
like to have their cake...
And eat it too.
...and eat it too, people.
(bleep) that.
The exes already have a face on,
and y'all just came from
the Shack of Secrets
and y'all looking at us like
y'all just seen a dead ghost.
Downstairs we saw
every conversation
anybody ever talked (bleep)
about us.
Jay's face looks like
he just saw, like,
a million dead puppies.
I thing in his eyes
I've never seen before.
Farrah, you said that you didn't
know that they hired a hooker,
calling me a hooker.
Are you (bleep)--
I haven't said anything
different when I was
yelling yesterday.
No, honey,
I am not a hooker.
But you're a porn star!
How can you even have
your opinion?
I am not a hooker.
The next person
that calls me--
Do not call me a hooker,
because you do not know me...
(bleep)!
...because you were the one
masturbating on a video!
(bleep) you.
Okay?
That's all I can say
about that.
If a ex pop out,
I (bleep).
Wait, I think
thaI think it is.■■at's what
Ohh...
Pretty sure that's a bottle.
Girl, get--
get them hands dirty, honey.
Oh, (bleep), (bleep), (bleep).
(indistinct chatter)
(bleep).
Wow!
(all exclaiming)
So we got another message,
and I'm thinking like,
pssh, ain't nothing good
gonna come out of this.
We haven't had no good news yet
in that damn bottle, man.
"And now for the icing
on the cake.
"Because revenge
is a dish best served cold,
"it's time to flip the script.
Exes, you now have the power."
(cheers and applause)
That's some (bleep).
Nice!
We find out that the exes
going to get the power
to send one single home.
And I'm thinking...
oh, (bleep)!
Tables have turned, bitches,
and I'm here to come for each
and every one of you.
♪♪
■88■■■■■■■■?■qq■q■qq■■q■■■■■■■■2
Not much here,
except the usual.
Wh
things up a bit?
Alexa...
"Fire"
by The Ohio Players
♪Fire (uh) (uh)♪
What if we turn it up a notch?
♪Fire (It's all about) (Uh, uh)♪
What if we go off the map?
♪Fire (Woo, woo, woo)♪
♪Fire♪
The all-new RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
Hello, there.
Do we go crunchy-cool
or golden Classic?
I know.
One for me and
one for you.
Now that's a sandwich!
Lay's.
Make Life Flavorful.
You can't put a price on love.
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
Hy-a-luronic Acid
Hyaluronic acid.
It's the skincare ingredient
that everyone is searching for!
And It's in here.
New from Revitalift:
Derm Intensives Hyaluronic
Acid Serum
With our highest concentration
of Hyaluronic Acid in a serum
Visibly plumps skin in
just one week
bounce back!
And reduces wrinkles for
younger-looking skin.
Powerful results
Validated by a panel
of dermatologists
New Revitalift Derm Intensives
Hyaluronic Acid Serum
From L'Oreal Paris
We're worth it.
♪♪
(announcer)
Welcome back.
(cheers and ap)
■w■er)
Now that the exes have
the power,
one of you (bleep)-talking
singles is going home.
About time!
So I'm confused what the (bleep)
is happening here,
but you gotta let me knSpicy!
I mean, you just (bleep) up
my whole damn dinner.
(Morgan)
Jay? Jay?
(bleep) has hit the fan
and I've been trying
to make it work with Jay.
And I'm like, at this point,
I don't think I'm gonna be able
to dig myself out of this one.
(whispering in)
I'm done.
(bleep) (bleep) no.
No, no, no, Morgan.
No, I'm done.
Morgan!
(all exclaim)
Oh, (bleep)!
No, like, I'm done, no, like--
Morgan, Morgan.
I'm literally done.
No, I'm done.
I mean, Morgan, my girl,
I don't know what you've done
karma-wise, but God bless you.
■ ■     May the Force be
with you, dear.
(announcer)
In a living room far, far away,
the exes lean into the dark side
as they strategize
which single
they should get revenge on.
I know you're
gonna say Farrah,
but you gotta look at it
from this point of view.
Yeah, she causes
a lot of (bleep),
but y'all let her.
Like, y'all let-- listen.
Y'all let her words
actually eat up.
Y'all, y'all take,
like-- y'all act like
her words matter.
You only got here yesterday.
That's what I'm saying.
Mm-hmm.
You haven't seen
the whole thing about her.
She is nasty
as a human being.
Nasty.
I haven't really got an
opportunity to talk to Darian.
He was hanging around
Malcolm a lot,
and everyone knows that Malcolm
comes with Diandra and Nurys.
You're not making it easy for me
to forgive you,
because I'm continuously
watching you around people
that I don't like.
♪♪
(sobbing)
I just don't think it's fair!
Morgan, you are much stronger
than this, babe.
Come on!
Okay.
You know what?
I said this whole entire time
I was not gonna reach
my breaking point.
And congratulations,
"Ex on the Beach."
You officially broke me.
What else can I do
to screw up?
I feel like
I screw up everything!
No.
No, you don't.
Just let her cry.
She just needs to cry,
honestly.
Let it out.
I think right now Morgan
actually feels
genuinely sorry and bad.
She hurt Jay's feelings,
and I think Jay has every reason
to feel the way he does.
♪♪
■■■■■■■■■■  (bleep)!
(sustained bleep echoing)
Now, eyeliner goes NYC-proof.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil
from Maybelline New York.
Smudge resistant.
Sweat resistant.
Waterproof.
Up to 36-hour we
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil.
Only from Maybelline New York.
Every year,
Team Rubicon enlists the help
eterans to provide relief
to communities
affenatural disasters.
Do it for those
who need your help.
Mountain Dew
is proud
to support
the efforts
of
Team Rubicon.
Let's Do.
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
Hello, there.
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
Do we go crunchy-cool
or golden Classic?
I know.
One for me and
one for you.
Now that's a sandwich!
Lay's.
Make Life Flavorful.
(announcer)
Welcome back.
Before the break,
the exes found out
that they all had power
for tomorrow's elimination,
which is bad news for some
of our misbehaved singles.
(Morgan)
You know, I tried so hard
■■■■
in this house
to be positive and happy.
'Cause the last thing
I wanted to do
was come in this house
and lose myself.
And now I feel so lost.
I know I don't have a say
with the exes,
but I want Corey out
before Farrah.
To me, he doesn't
contribute anything.
He has the personality
of a (bleep) pet rock.
And I feel like
Jay's pissed with you
just because, like--
Why would he be pissed
with me?
I feel like he's pissed
at you and her because--
Not at me.
She was kissing back.
It wasn't like a--
she said it was a snipe.
It wasn't a snipe.
It wasn't a snipe at all.
When you're in this house,
you kind of know
that evI mean, yeah,onna be
revshe could focus on Jay.,..■s
But honestly, like,
what's she gonna look at?
You know what I'm saying?
It's hard for me
to deal with the house
and all this
and me and you haven't
gotten anything,
like, resolved.
Resolved.
That (bleep) pisses me off
'cause it's like
I'm over here dying inside.
Darian knows that I do not allow
a man to not be accountable
fowrongdanise
thatt go it again.
Like, I need you to repent
to me like I'm Jesus.
When are you gonna fight
for me here
instead of involving yourself
in (bleep) that don't
(bleep) matter?
When the (bleep)
are you gonna fight for me?
You don't even know
what you want.
When we originally broke up,
she left me, literally.
But now I feel like she kind of
wants the best of both worlds.
The onlymatters
is me
can't strictly talk
about me and you right now,
then I will just go to bed.
That's fine.
Okay. Good-bye.
Like, this is (bleep).
That (bleep) again, man.
Let it go.
Are you good with us being done,
yes or no?
Of course not, Janelle.
I feel like we're still
up in the air.
It could go left,
it could go right.
At the end of the day,
Yeah,I'm my own man. know?
I'm gonna make my own decisions.
♪ One light ♪
♪ So co raise your head up
to the sky ♪
♪ Aye-aye-aye-aye ♪♪
We good now?
That is so cute.
(Farrah)
Look at you
and your cute breakfast.
■■■■ up!
and sausage.
So you haven't got sausage
in a while, so open up.
(both laughing)
(Sha)
That was a good one, huh?
Mmm.
Pretty good, huh?
It's tricky.
I really love it.
I'm just gonna go eat up
all my sausage.
See you later.
We both haven't got sausage
in a long time.
(Chad groans)
You know when you're
hung over
and you get ready
and you don't even
remember getting ready
but you just kind of come to
as you're looking good
and you're like, "Yeah"?
Yeah.
It's nice.
♪♪
It's so weird that an OG
might leave.
Might? Is.
So if I am really up
for elimination,
I'm not worried about it,
but I'm prepared,
and I'm G
a pantsuit tonight.
In all Farrah-ness,
I don't really feel like
I should be leaving.
Punted her straight
in the pooter.
I don't think I did.
What am I gonna do
to a girl's crotch?
The whole thing with Nazarian
or whatever her name is--
3v3v3va  Nazar-- N-Na--
Something with an N.
Just keep thinking her name
is like Nazarian.
It's like my plastic surgeon.
I really-- I'd rather be
thinking about that
than whatever she's about,
so...
What's up, gangsta?
What's going on?
Talk to me.
I'm just, like,
drained emotionally.
I just didn't wanna get
to that point yesterday
and I did,
and now I feel like
I, like, can't be myself.
What do you want
with us?
I don't know.
You don't trust me anymore.
It's like--
You honestly believe
that I don't trust you
at all?
I don't know.
(sighs)
I just wish you were
more honest with me.
I would prefer the truth.
Not 10%, 50%, 90%.
Give me the whole
damn thing.
Just wanna say sorry.
I didn't wanna put you
through all this.
Do I still want affection
and touch her all the time
and hug and (bleep)?
Hell yeah.
So I'll give her a shot.
I'll give her a chance again.
But...
I still care about you.
It's like, are you happier
with me here?
Yeah, what are they gonna do?
Send me a new blond?
(announcer)
We know where Jay stands,
but the rest of the exes
are still making up their minds.
I just wanna know where--
what-- like, where your
heads are at
and why you would--
you know, like,
who you guys wanna vote out
and, like, why?
(Diandra)
The only singles on the chopping
block are Corey and Farrah.
Corey because Morgan
wants him out.
She doesn't feel that she can
continue her relationship
ay while he's here.
And Farrah is
on the chopping block.
It's 'cause she kicked my girl
in the vagina and she needs
to (bleep) off.
Morgan's like,
"Someone help me, please."
But she's not actually
physically getting attacked,
and it's bull(bleep).
You know I get your side,
and I feel so bad for Morgan
that she's gotten bull(bleep)
after bull(bleep)
after bull(bleep).
But to be honest,
she did not get
this physically attacked.
That's so (bleep) up that any
of you guys are even deciding
for even the slightest
(bleep) bit.
Seriously?
I don't understand why people
wanna get Corey out.
Corey hasn't done anything.
Faa crazy,
delusional bitch.
■#■#     She's the one
that's the problem.
It's the craziest thing
you guy
We're supposed to be exes
and we're supposed
to stick together, correct?
Correct, and none
of you guys had my back.
It's the biggest
bull(bleep) ever.
Even though I know
she hurt you,
and, like, Farrah did
do things wrong,
everyone's done
a couple things wrong,
and at this point, like,
it's like we're not all
gonna come to one.
I think we should all just vote
what we think at this point.
So I'm just gonna go ahead
and crush Farrah just because
I feel like Farrah,
if you're gonna respect her,
she'll respectight back.
She treats all of us pretty good
other than the people
that she doesn't like,
which is everyone
for the most part.
I shouldn't have to (bleep)--
this should be easy.
It shouldn't
even be a question.
I totally understand why
you want her out.
I wish y'all would just
talk it out.
But you don't even
wanna talk to me, so...
I thought she did try
to talk to her.
She did try
to talk to Farrah,
and Farrah just blew--
I already know
I'm the bigger person.
I don't need to.
I'm not going up
to the bitch again.
And yes, I will
call her a bitch
'cause she's a bitch.
Like, I really don't care.
(Nurys)
It sucks to see that people
don't have my back.
I haven't done anything
to deserve that.
(sobbing)
HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN'T GET
HIGH SPEED INTERNET WHERE YOU
LIVE? WELL@>N WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITE INTERNET WHEREVER YOU
LIVE. HUGHESNET GEN 5 IS FAST.
YOU'LL GET 25MBPS, PLUS BUILT IN
WIFI, AND THERE'S NO HARD DATA
LIMITS. SO, WHEREVER YOU LIVE,
NONN DO MORE OF
EVERYTHING YOU LOVE ONLINE.
CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, STAY
INFORMED, WATCH THE LATEST
VIDEOS, AND HELP YOUR KIDS GET■
AMERICA'S NUMBER ONE CHOICE FOR
SATELLITE INTERNET. ACT NOW TO
SAVE $99 INSTANTLY WITH OUR
LIMITED TIME OFFER AND GET FREE
STANDARD INSTALLATION TOO. SO,
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR? GET
HUGHESNET GEN5. TO ORDER, CALL
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN. BE
SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR HOME PHONE
SERVICE, TOO. CALL THE NUMBER ON
This is Dell Cinema technology
with CinemaStream for
less buffering,
CinemaSound for
brilliant clarity,
Shop the biggest
Presidents Day ever
at Dell.com.
♪
At last, one red that works on
everyone.
New Made for All lip color from
Maybelline New York.
Tested on 50 skin tones.
New Made for All.l. ■J■J■J
Only from Maybelline New York.
You can't put a price on love.
■2■2
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
♪♪
Today is the day that the exes
finally have the power.
Now the singles get a taste
their own medicine.
One of you mother(bleep)
is going home.
■You're gone,
Well, I'm just gonna go ahead
and crush Farrah
just because I'm cool with her
and I'm just gonna go ahead
and not even deal
with the whole Corey thi
jusso■■cauwith aloodl with her
and I'm just gonna go ahead
■
I respe(sighs)
♪♪
Tonight, I am cutting Corey
because I think
that he came here
with a mission to stir up
feelings with Morgan.
I think that's
kind of passed, so...
♪♪
(Corey)
Honestly, I think that people
are, like, trying
to protect Morgan,
but she's, like, you know,
a little bitter at this point,
I think, and she, like, wants
to get me out now.
(Farrah)
I'm shocked that I would even be
up to be eliminated, really.
?         But as I am,
I'm ready to defend myself.
I'm here to stay.
What up?
What up, everybody?
Looking good.
(applause)
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■)
Now, before we get started,
I want to say something.
There's any more confrontations
that get physical,Beach."
you will be sent home.
We're all about love
here, baby.
All right, let's get down
to business.
Singles, we're gon' do things
a little bit differently
tonight.
Earlier today, the exes voted
for which single they wanted
to crush or cut.
■&■2■&■2■&■2■&■2■&■2■&■2■&■2■&■■
The sing■Treceived
ll be se
Crush votes, like y'all know,
cancels out cut votes.
And if the vote
results in a tie,
the power will revert
to the remaining singles.
■■■nd new l■   rekindle with a,
or just say (bleep) love.
By the end of your time here,
we're gonna put you through
the ultimate test.
I've tried real hard to campaign
to get Corey out of this house.
Be able to a!■
Before we get to these votes,c.
anybody wanna say anything?
I would like to make a speech.
Wow. Okay.
(Romeo)
A speech.
(Farrah)
Yeah.
So it's a "keep Farrah"
campaign.
But does she forget
we already voted?
If I, Farrah,
am here to stay,
I pledge unlimited
grocery shopping,
live-in maid.
Also lots more toilet paper,
cleaner, and air spray.
We gotta wrap it up
in a second.
Okay, all right.
All who voted for me
to be eliminated
will be on trash duty
and be shunned.
■Aaa■■
(laughter)
Honestly, in my heart of hearts,
I don't want either Farrah
or Corey to go.
Farrah, we gotta take
a seat right there.
Thank you.
All right.
(cheers and applause)
Whoo!
Thank you.
(giggling)
So funny.
All right, all right,
we gon' get back to it.
Let's get started.
Jozea.
■C■C■C
You already know what it is.
You good.
Nothing's in there.
No cut or no crush.
Yes.
You are safe, Jozea.
Maya, Malcolm,
Nicole, Cheyenne, Chad...
■t have nothing
in your pineapple.
(applause)
Which means you are safe.
We will got a lot of chips
still out there.
♪♪
With that being said,
Morgan,
please step up
to your pineapple.
♪♪
So how would you like
the vogo tonight?
I honestly would like Corey
to go home.
It's nothing against him,
but I have three exes
in the house.
Three is enough.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
You got a chip.
But it's a crush.
lause)
Duh.        But it's a crush.
Have a seat.
So, Janelle,
you've been in the middle
of a■8drama this week.
Mm-hmm.
Why don't you step up
to your pineapple?
Sure thing.
See how this goes.
♪♪
(laughter)
Think you have  a?
Maybe.
You never know.
Let's get to it.
Hold on.
You got a chip.
But it's a crush.
(applause)
Wow!
I said actions, people.
I said actions.
You got a crush,
which is a sign of love.
(bleep).
You better crush all this.
You are safe.
Have a sanelle.
I'm just saying.
Look at smile, man.
You see that?
Changes everything.
He's trying
to get his (bleep).
We finally got a chip.
YeahThank you.y is.
(Nelson)
Hey, Romeo.
I don't think he's the one
that put that crush vote
in there.
(all exclaiming)
Oh, (bleep).
Oh, (bleep)!
ç,
When Taco Bell's
Nacho Fries disappear...
Where did you go?
...one man must bring them back.
♪
♪Daddy's gonna bring
you Nacho Fries... ♪
Now Serving.
[BONG]
♪ ♪
Let's face it,
the world
could use some warmth.
♪ ♪
Juicy, sizzling steak.
Hand-tossed original dough.
Fresh cut onions,
crunchy green peppers,
a delicious
four cheese blend,
and our creamy Philly sauce.
All on the best
Philly Cheesesteak
you can get on a pizza.
Right now get
the new Philly
or any large specialty
Papa John's pizza
for just 12 bucks.
Hy-a-luronic Acid
Hyaluronic acid.
It's the skincare ingredient
that everyone is searching for!
And It's in here.
New from Revitalift:
Derm Intensives Hyaluronic
Acid Serum
With our highest concentration
of Hyaluronic Acid in a serum
Visibly plumps skin in
just one week
bounce back!
And reduces wrinkles for
younger-looking skin.
Powerful results
Validated by a panel
of dermatologists
New Revitalift Derm Intensives
Hyaluronic Acid Serum
From L'Oreal Paris
We're worth it.
Look! It's a Beluga whale.
Hmm...
I don't know.
That's it.
Suit up!
♪
Ha-ha! Watch the fur!
Look!
♪
ahhh...
Can we keep him?
What do you see in
your Cheetos?
On tour, every second counts.
I need great without the wait.
New Elvive
Rapid Reviver
Deep Conditioners.
L'Oréal's patented conditioners
work fast with no leave-in time.
Enriched with
damage-repairing serum.
2x easier detangling
2x less breakage
than with a leading conditioner.
Works deep. Repairs damage fast.
Hair's transformed instantly.
New Rapid Reviver
Deep Conditioners.
Elvive revives damaged hair.
We're worth it.
♪♪
♪ And everywhere I go ♪
♪ There's always
something to remind me ♪
♪ Of another
place and time ♪
♪♪
Hey, Romeo, Of another
I don't think he's the one
that put that crush vote
in there.
Oh.
I did.
(all exclaiming)
Oh, (bleep).
Wow.
Winning!
So you gave
the crush vote
to Janelle?
■@
Yes, I did.
What I respect about her
is that she apologized
ra.
I could not do anything
but respect that,
so■2
■
I gave you that crush vote.
is that she apologized
ra.        (applause)
Darian ain't getting
his (bleep).
I am pissed because Darian was
going to fully take the credit
for that crush, but instead
of wasting it on someone
that you barely even know,
it's like, put it towards me
to show me that, like,
you care.
Corey, please step up
to your pineapple.
If I had to guess,
you got some chips
in there.
Yeah.
Let's get to it.
First chip, cut.
Got another chip...
which is a cut.
You got two cut votes,
which means you're on
the hot seat.
Take a seat.
I might be going home because
of, like, her messiness,
and it's just not
that I would have to
potentially go home.
It'd be stupid for them
to kick me out of the house
'cause I never cause drama.
Like, I'm here to date,
you know, maybe find love.
So, next, Farrah.
Please step up
to your pineapple.
You think you have
I mean, I hope I havesh votes,
some crush votes. cut votes?■
All right, you ready
to get to it?
Yeah.
First one.
I'm so over Farrah!
You're giving everybody
a hard time.
You are a (bleep) person
to everybody.
You kicked one
of my closest friends
he house in her vagina.
You need to get
the (bleep) out.
(announcer)
Previously on "Ex on the Beach,"
ten incredibly single
and available reality stars
1#1#■#1#1#1#1#1#1#1#1#
are looking for love
while living with their exes.
Jozea and his ex Rob had an
emotional reunion at the beach.
Are you about to cry?
Aww!
(announcer)
Farrah wouldn't let
Nurys and Darian
have a private conversation.
I don't know why the (bleep)
you're coming out here.
(announcer)
So Farrah kicked her
in the privates.
Anto vote out Farrahet
in the flipped elimination
when the exes got the power
to vote out one of the singles.
after trying to get in the way
Coreof Morgan and Jay's seat■
relationship.
So now him and Farrah are both
in fear of elimination,
and one of them is going home.
♪♪
(thunder rumbling)
♪ Who knew that
the devil wore red? ♪
♪ Silk dress, yeah,
she always is a mess ♪
♪ She more petty
than the rest ♪
♪ Heartbreaker... ♪♪
(announcer)
Welcome back.
It's elimination night,
and this time, the exes are<<e
by giving them
a crush vote or a cut vote.
Nelson put his crush
in Janelle's pineapple
as a way to thank her
for taking the high road
after her fight with Diandra.
Darian tried to take credit
for it until he got called out.