IF HE TREATS HER THIS WAY.
>> DOES SHE HAVE A SECRET.
>> YOU'RE ACTING LIKE A
PROSTITUTE.
>> ARE YOU CHEATING WITH HIM.
>> SHE CHEATED WHEN SHE WAS
PREGNANT.
>> WHAT'S UP WITH THAT MAN.
>> IT'S TIME TO "FACE THE TR
TRUTH."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Vivica: EVER SINCE DON
DROPPED 125 POUNDS --
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Vivica: MEN APPROACH HER AND
TELL HER SHE LOCKS LIKE MARYLIN
MONROE.
SHE'S LIVING LIFE AS A BLOND
BOMBSHELL.
HER HUSBAND, BRANDON, IS IN
LIVING HELL.
>> Vivica: DON'S LOOK AND LIFE
CHANGED AFTER GASTRIC BYPASS
SURGERY.
SHE IS CONSTANTLY GETTING HIT ON
AND IT'S REVEALED HER HUSBAND AS
SHE HAS NEVER SEEN HIM.
JEALOUS.
HE ACCUSES HER OF CHEATING.
DON SAYS SHE HAS STARTED
PARTYING ALL NIGHT.
HE SAYS HE'S NOT JEALOUS BUT
WORRIED WHO HIS WIFE HAS BECOME.
WILL THIS MARRIAGE BE NO MORE
BECAUSE DON HAS GONE MONROE.
[LAUGHING]
>> Vivica: SO, DON, DO GENTLEMEN
PREFER BLONDS?
>> FROM MY EXPERIENCE I WOULD
SAY ABSOLUTELY YES.
>> Vivica: YOU USE TO HAVE
DARKER HAIR, CORRECT.
>> CORRECT.
>> Vivica: YA, WHEN YOU DID THE
GASTRIC BYPASS THEN WHAT MADE
YOU DECIDE TO GO BLOND?
>> ONE OF THE SIDE AFFECTS WAS
MY HAIR FELL OUT.
>> Vivica: WOW.
>> ABOUT MONTH THROW YOU LOSE
YOUR HAIR.
>> Vivica: YOU LOSE YOUR HAIR?
>> FOR LACK OF PROTEIN AND
NUTRITION YOUR HAIR FALLS OUT.
>> IT'S PART OF IT.
YOUR HAIR LOOKS BEAUTIFUL.
HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN SINCE THE
SURGERY?
>> THREE YEARS.
>> CONGRATULATIONS ON
MAINTENANCE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Vivica: YOU WERE BEAUTIFUL
BEFORE.
BEAUTIFUL NOW.
THE TRANSFORMATION OF SELF
CONFIDENCE HOW HAS THAT BEEN FOR
YOU?
>> INCREDIBLE.
I FEEL LIKE A NEW WOMAN.
I FEEL LIKE I'M 25 AGAIN.
>> AWESOME.
>> YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE 25.
>> THANK YOU.
>> BRANDON, WITH YOUR WIFE
STKP-G THROUGH THIS
TRANSFORMATION YOU FEEL SHE HAS
CHEATED ON HER?
>> I NEVER FELT LIKE MY WIFE
CHEATED ON ME.
I KNOW SHE GETS MORE ATTENTION.
I'M CONCERNED ABOUT HER
BEHAVIOR.
GOING OUT, HANGING OUT WITH HER
FRIENDS.
I'M A LITTLE CONCERNED.
>> BOTTOM LINE, ARE YOU CHEATING
ON HIM.
LET'S CUT TO THE CHASE.
>> NO, HE ACCUSED ME.
>> ARE YOU CHEATING ON HIM?
>> I AM NOT.
>> THERE ARE ISSUES THAT HAVE
CAUSED THE CONCERNS.
FOR EXAMPLE YOU WENT TO LUNCH
WITH A CLIENT.
THINK ONE TIME THE CLIENT WAS ON
SPEAKERPHONE.
YOU HAPPENED TO BE THERE AND THE
CLIENT CALLED YOU BABY IN THE
MESSAGE.
>> YES.
FIRST OF ALL IF I'M CHEATING
WILL MY LOVER BE ON
SPEAKERPHONE.
>> GOOD POINT.
>> FIRST OF ALL BEFORE I'M
BEAUTIFUL I'M INTELLIGENT.
>> YOUR HUSBAND LOVES YOU.
WHY IS A MAN CAWING MY WIFE
BABY.
>> TRUE.
HE ADDRESSED ME.
IT'S A REAL ESTATE CLIENT.
WE HAD LUNCH.
I CAN'T HELP IF HE CALLS ME
BABY.
I HAVE BEEN CALLED A LOT WORST.
>> YOU NEVER SHARED  A
CONVERSATION WITH A WOMAN,
THANKS, HONEY.
>> YOU NEVER DONE THAT?
>> NOT REALLY.
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL IF A WOMAN
CALLED ME BABY.
>> Vivica: HOW WOULD YOU FEEL?
>> DEPENDS ON WHO THE WOMAN WAS.
QUITE PERSONALLY I'M NOT
THREATENED BY NO WOMAN.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> IS THAT THE NEW FOUND
CONFIDENCE OR BEEN LIKE THAT THE
ENTIRE RELATIONSHIP?
>> WHEN I MET HIM I WAS 37.
HE WAS 25.
I WALKED UP HIM TO AND
APPROACHED HIM.
I SAID YOU.
I NEED YOU IN MY LIFE.
IT WAS LOVE AT FIRST SIGHT.
I PURSUED HIM.
I WAS A BIG GIRL.
I LOOKED LIKE THAT PICTURE UP
THERE.
IT DIDN'T STOP ME ONE BIT.
HE HAD OTHER WOMEN --
>> YOU HAVE BEEN CONFIDENT.
>> ALWAYS.
HE HAD OTHER WOMEN IN HIS LIFE.
HE COULD LIKE ME OR NOT.
HE HAD THE OPLGS TO GET TO KNOW
ME OR NOT.
HE CHOSE TO.
THE REST IS HISTORY FROM THERE.
>> BRANDON, YOU HAVE A ISSUE
BECAUSE SOMETIMES HER CONFIDENT
AND HER BEING NOISE IS TAKEN FOR
FLIRTATION.
>> WE HAVE BEEN TO CONCERTS.
SHE GOES UP TO ARTSISTS AND TAKE
PICTURES AND HUG THEM.
I UNDERSTAND I'M NOT THAT TYPE
OF JEALOUS GUY.
SHE KNOWS THIS.
>> Vivica: I UNDERSTAND ONE TIME
SHE WAS AT LUNCH AND YOU CALLED
HER 18 TIMES.
>> I'M OFF WORK.
SHE IS OUT WITH FRIENDS.
HEY, I LIKE TO SPEND TIME WITH
MY WIFE TOO.
>> I GET THAT.
BRANDON, 18 TIMES.
>> I'M NOT SURE IT WAS AS WELL
TIMES.
>> SHE WAS.
>> WHEN I LOOKED AT MY PHONE.
IT WAS ARE YOU OKAY.
EVERYTHING ALRIGHT.
IT WAS MORE OF A CONCERN FOR MY
SAFETY.
THAT IS NO CONCERN.
I HAVE A LICENSE TO CARRIE.
TRUST ME I TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, DON, WE SEE YOU WEAR
THE PANTS HERE.
HAVE THESE ALWAYS BEEN THE
DYNAMICS BETWEEN YOU TWO?
>> I WASN'T PHYSICALLY
CONFIDENT.
I WAS ASHAMED THE WAY I LOOKED.
I COULDN'T FIND CLOTHING THAT
LOOKED RIGHT.
I WOULD CRY BECAUSE NOTHING
WOULD FIT ME.
NOW I HAVE ANOTHER CONFIDENCE.
I LOOK IN THE MIRROR AND SAY, I
LIKE WHAT I SEE.
I THANK MY SURGEON FOR HELPING
ME ACHIEVE THESE GOALS.
I'M LIVING THESE GOALS.
AS I HAVE AGED I HAVE GOTTEN
BETTER.
WHERE WOMEN LOSE WHAT THEY HAD
IN YOUTH, I REGAINED MINE AND
GOT WHAT I DIDN'T HAVE BACK
THEN.
>> ALRIGHT, GIRLFRIEND.
>> Vivica: DON SAYS SHE FINALLY
FEELS BEAUTIFUL.
BRANDON SAYS HER MEYER LYNN
PERSONA CAUSES FIGHTS TO GET
UGLY QUICK.
>> Vivica: DON, BRANDON HAS
ACCUSED OF YOU ACTING LIKE A
PROSTITUTE.
>> I AM WHO I
New Lysol Wipes are crazy
strong.
Don't believe us?
We got this workout class to
compare them to Clorox.
Wow!
Feel the strength
of new Lysol Wipes.
Dude!
Are you looking at this?
Can I take those?
No.
Lysol. What it takes
to protect.®
Little Dakota's nose was
quivering in fear.
Because it knew an ordinary
tissue was near.
The fiery tissue left her nose
sore and red.
So Dad slayed the problem with
Puffs Plus Lotion, instead.
Puffs have pillowy softness for
Dakota's tender nose.
With lotion to comfort and
soothe when she blows.
Don't get burned by ordinary
tissues.
A nose in need deserves
Puffs, indeed.
( ♪♪ )
Do you believe in romance?
Romance, the fragrance
by Ralph Lauren.
>> Vivica: IF YOU LIKE OUR TRUTH
TEAM HELP YOU SETTLE A COP
TPHREUBGT AND FIND A REAL
CONSTRUCTIVE RESOLUTION CALL OR
E-MAIL US.
>> Vivica: IT'S TIME TO F "FACE
THE TRUTH" ARE YOU READY.
>> Vivica: DON DROPPED
125 POUNDS.
SHE'S READY TO DROP HER HUSBAND
BRANDON IF HE CONTINUES TO TREAT
HER LIKE A FLIRTATIOUS CHEAP.
DON, YOU SAY BRANDON HAS ACCUSED
OF YOU ACTING LIKE A PROSTITUTE.
>> YES.
I HAVE A PARTICULAR FRIEND WHO
IS KIND OF OUT THERE.
WE HAVE A LOT OF FUN.
SHE ASKED ME TO PLAY POKER WITH
HER ONE NIGHT.
WE WEPT OUT.
I SAID I WOULD BE HOME BY 2:00.
IT WAS 4:00 IN THE MORNING.
SHE WAS UNCONSCIOUS.
I WAS TRYING TO WAKE HER UP TO
GET HER HOME.
IN THE TIME I ATTEMPTED TO WAKE
HER UP TO GO HOME I GET TEXT
MESSAGES WHERE I WAS CALLED A
DISRESPECTFUL [BEEP].
I WAS ACTING LIKE A WOMAN OF THE
NIGHT.
IRRESPONSIBLE AND NOT MOTHERLY
LIKE.
TO ME THAT'S BEING CALLED A
PROSTITUTE.
>> Vivica: WE HAVE THAT TEXT
THAT BRANDON SENT YOU.
IT READS.
YOU ARE ONE PIECE OF WORK.
I HOPE YOU FIND WHAT YOU ARE
LOOKING FOR IN THOSE STREETS.
YOU'RE ACTING LIKE A WOMAN OF
THE NIGHT.
>> WOW.
>> CAN YOU ACCEPT THE FACT MAYBE
HE WAS TICKED OFF.
MAYBE HE'S TICKED OFF YOU HAVE A
KID AT HOME.
YOU'RE OUT GAL VANAVANTING.
>> YES.
I SENT HIM A PICTURE OF THE
POKER TABLE.
I ADMITTED IT WAS A MISTAKE
GOING OUT WITH THIS FRIEND.
>> WAS THIS A OLD FRIEND OR NEW
FRIEND?
>> I BARLEY MET HER IN AUGUST.
>> THEY SAY WHO YOU HANG AROUND
WITH.
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I AM WHO I AM NO MATTER WHO I AM
WITH.
I AM ALWAYS MYSELF.
>> DOES THAT HAPPEN COMMONLY.
LOST THE WEIGHT AND NEW FRIENDS.
GOING OUT AND PARTYING MORE AND
DRINKING MORE?
>> CAN I EXPLAIN.
I HAVE BEEN OUT TWO TIMES IN
ELEVEN YEARS WITHOUT THIS MAN.
>> BRANDON, WHY DID YOU SEND
THIS TEXT?
>> THIS WAS THE SECOND TIME SHE
WAS OUT WITH THIS FRIEND.
EVERY TIME THIS FRIEND COMES
OVER ALL OF A SUDDEN HER FRIEND
HAS PROBLEMS WITH HER
RELATIONSHIP.
SHE COMES TO OUR HOUSE WITH HER
KID.
NOW SHE'S TRYING TO GET OUT OF
THE HOUSE AND TAKE MY WIFE OUT
OF THE HOUSE AT 10:00, 12:00,
2:00, 3:00, 4:00, 5:00 IN THE
MORNING.
>> I TOLD HER I CAN'T GO OUT
WITH ANYMORE.
I WILL END UP DIVORCED FROM YOUR
BEHAVIOR.
>> Vivica: YOU GOT ANOTHER TEXT.
>> A LOT.
>> Vivica: IT READS.
ARE YOU SO FULL OF FWOOP.
YOU'RE ONE DISRESPECTING [BEEP]
>> WOW, BRANDON.
>> WOW.
>> YOU TALK TO HER LIKE THIS
OFTEN?
>> NO, AT THIS POINT I'M LIVE I
DID.
YOU KNOW.
>> YES.
>> IT'S A WEEK NIGHT.
I HAVE TO GO TO WORK THE NEXT
MORNING.
I'M A CONCERNED HUSBAND.
I CARE ABOUT MY WOULD I HAVE.
IN THE BEGINNING OF MY
RELATIONSHIP SHE HAD A PROBLEM
WITH ME GOING OUT.
IT'S DANGEROUS OUT THIS.
I'M CONCERNED ABOUT YOUR SAFETY.
SAME HERE.
I'M A CONCERNED HUSBAND.
>> DID YOU THINK AT ANY POINT I
WILL STEP OUT OF THE POKER GAME
AND TEXT HIM.
>> TO BE HONEST WITH YOU I
THOUGHT HE WOULD TRUST ME ENOUGH
AND IT WAS THE A ISSUE.
>> HAS HE EVER DISRESPECTED YOU
HOEUBG THAT BEFORE THAT MOMENT.
>> NOT REALLY, NO.
>> YOU HAVE CALLED HIM NAMES?
>> MAYBE ONE OR TWICE.
>> HE EVEN TALKED ABOUT MY MAN
PARTS IN FRONT OF HER FRIENDS.
THAT WAS LOW AND DISRESPECT
FULL.
>> I SAID I CAN CALL NAMES TOO.
IT HURTS.
YOU WANT TO HURT.
HAVE A TASTE OF YOUR OWN
MEDICINE.
>> SOMETIMES AFTER SOMEONE HAS
GASTRIC BYPASS SURGERY AND LOSES
WEIGHT IT CAUSES PROBLEMS IN THE
RELATIONSHIP.
WERE YOU WARNED?
>> I WAS WARNED.
I WENT TO SUPPORT GROUPS AND
WARNED ME.
I SAID, NO, I HAVE A GREAT
MARRIAGE, GREAT MAN.
HE TRUSTS ME AND KNOWS ME.
THIS IS ABOUT ME REGAINING MY
HEALTH.
I NEVER ANTICIPATED LOOKING THIS
WAY.
I THOUGHT I WOULD LOOK THE SAME
WAY JUST LESS OF ME.
>> Vivica: IT HAS IMPACTED YOUR
RELATIONSHIP.
>> YES.
HE'S A INTROVERT AND PREFERS TO
STAY HOME AND WANTS ME HOME TOO.
I AM TOO FABULOUS TO STAY HOME.
BOTTOM LINE.
>> Vivica: CAN THIS MARRIAGE BE
SAVED?
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> COMING UP.
>> BRANDON YOU ARE WORRIED HER
DRINKING IS OUT OF CONTROL.
>> HOW MUCH DO YOU DRINK.
>> I LIKE TO HAVE FUN AND PARTY.
>> I HAD ABOUT 30 POUNDS OF
SKIN.
HOW COULD YOU T THINK I WOULD GT
NAKED IN FRONT OF
Prestige creams not living up to
the hype?
One jar shatters the
competition.
ay Regenerist hydrates skin
tter than creams
costing over $100, $200, and
even $400.
Fact check this ad in Good
Housekeeping.
Olay.
( ♪♪ )
Do you believe in romance?
Romance, the fragrance
by Ralph Lauren.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Vivica: DON WENT FROM
OVERWEIGHT BRUNNET TO CURVY
PLATINUM BLOND LIKE MAYOR LONG N
MONROE.
HER HEALTH AND SELF-ESTEEM IS
BETTER BUT HER MARRIAGE IS
WORST.
BRANDON YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT HER
DRINKING.
>> YES.
I SEE MY WIFE OUT WITH OTHER
FRIENDS AND IS INTOXICATED AND
STAGGERING.
I'M CONCERNED SHE IS PUTTING
HERSELF IN A HORRIBLE SITUATION.
>> Vivica: I WANT TO ASK A
QUESTION OF ROSIE QUICK.
WHEN YOU HAVE A GASTRIC SURGERY
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSE TO DRINK A
LOT.
>> YOU'RE SUPPOSE TO BE OFF OF
ALCOHOL AND SUGARS.
OTHER YOU GET ADDICTED TO
ALCOHOL OR SUGARS.
THE ABSORPTION OF OUR STOMACH,
THEY TAKE 80% OUT.
A LITTLE ALCOHOL AND YOU'RE
TIPSY.
YOU GIVE ME HALF A GLASS OF WINE
AND HELLO, I'M HERE.
IT CHANGES EVERYTHING.
YOU HAVE TO BE VERY CAREFUL WITH
THE GASTRIC SLEEVE.
WHAT YOU EAT IMPACTS THE WAY YOU
ACT.
>> DON, HOW MUCH DO YOU DRINK?
>> I LIKE TO HAVE FUN AND PARTY.
HE KNOWS THAT.
WE DRINK TOGETHER.
WHEN I GO OUT WITH FRIENDS AND
HAVE A FEW DRINKS I HAVE A HIGH
TOLERANCE AND I DRINK PROBABLY A
LITTLE TOO MUCH.
>> MAYBE A FEW DRINKS IF YOU'RE
OUT.
>> YES.
I REALIZE I SHOULDN'T DRINK AT
ALL.
NOT FOR ANY REASON OF ADDICTION
BUT MORE SO IT CUSSES ULCERS.
IF I GET AN ULCER IN MY LITTLE
STOMACH IT WILL KILL ME.
>> DO YOU GET CRAVINGS.
>> I FEEL I NEED A STKREUFRPBG
WHEN I'M FIGHTING WITH HIM AND I
NEED A DRINK.
IT MAKES ME HAPPY.
>> HOW YOUR INTIMATE LIFE.
>> THAT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
WHEN I WAS A BIG GIRL HE MADE ME
FEEL BEAUTIFUL.
I ASKED HIM IF I COULD MAKE HIS
BABY AT 39 YEARS OLD.
WE DID.
WE HAD A GREAT SEX LIFE.
THINGS HAVE CHANGED THE LAST FEW
MONTHS.
WE HAVE A GOOD INTIMATE LIFE.
NOW HE'S, I DON'T KNOW HAS
PULLED BACK A LITTLE BIT.
>> BRANDON, IS THAT TRUE.
>> NO THE PASSION IS STILL
THERE.
I LOVE THIS WOMAN.
THE PASSION IS THERE.
>> DON, WHY DO YOU FEEL HE HAS
PULLED BACK THE LAST COUPLE OF
MONTHS.
>> IT'S MY PERSONAL FEELINGS.
MAYBE IT'S HOW I FEEL THINGS
AREY AREEMOTIONALLY.
HE'S NOT SENSITIVE AND
CONTROLLING BUT MORE DOMINATING
AND CONTROLLING.
>> I UNDERSTAND YOUR JOURNEY
LOSING SO MUCH WEIGHT.
YOU GO FROM A PLACE YOU'RE NOT
PHYSICAL BEAUTIFUL.
NOW YOU HAVE A NEW PROBLEM THE
LOOSE SKIN.
DOES THAT AFFECT HOW YOU FEEL.
>> YES.
I GUESS THAT ANGERS ME ABOUT THE
CHEATING.
I TOLD HIM AND EXPRESSED MY
DEEPEST IN SECURITIES.
THE FACT I HAVE ABOUT 30 POUNDS
OF EXTRA SKIN.
HOW COULD YOU THINK I COULD GET
NAKED IN FRONT OF ANYONE.
I HOPE HE WOULDN'T THINK I WOULD
CHEAT ON HIM THE WAY I FEEL
ABOUT HIM.
HE'S MY EVERYTHING.
I LOVE THIS MAN MORE THAN THE
SUN, MOON, STARS, AND BEACH I
LIVE ACROSS FROM.
>> YOU HEAR THIS BRANDON.
>> YES, BRANDON.
>> HE KNOWS IT I DO EVERYTHING
FOR HIM.
I GET UP AN HOUR BEFORE HIM TO
MAKE HIS BREAKFAST, LUNCH, DO
HIS LAUNDRY.
I AM A MOM AND HAVE A FULL-TIME
JOB.
>> ARE YOU DOING TOO MUCH.
>> MAYBE I AM.
>> HOW MANY NEW FRIENDS HAVE YOU
ACQUIRED SINCE YOU HAVE ACQUIRED
THIS GODDESS.
>> THEY DON'T HAVE ANYTHING THE
WAY I LOOK.
>> THAT'S NOT MY QUESTION.
>> ONLY TWO.
>> IS THAT TRUE.
>> I MET THEM BOTH THROUGH
SCHOOL.
>> Vivica: ONLY TWO NEW FRIENDS,
BRANDON?
>> YES.
TWO NEW FRIENDS SHE HAS HUNG OUT
WITH AND BEEN OUT ON THE TOWN
WITH DRINKING.
>> Vivica: DO YOU LIKE THEM?
>> THE ONE FRIEND I DON'T LIKE
EVERY TIME SHE COMES AROUND SHE
WANTS MY WIFE TO PLAY POKER.
>> NOW I CAN'T HAVE FRIENDS.
YOU'RE THAT INSECURE I CAN'T
HAVE FRIENDS.
>> THE FRIENDS HAVE TO BE
RESPECTFUL TOO OF THE HOUSE AND
OUR FAMILY.
>> THE WHOLE REASON I'M HERE IS
I FEEL HE'S INSECURE AND
JEALOUS.
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> Vivica: WHEN WE COME BACK
THIS COUPLE WILL FACE THE TRUTH.
>> Vivica: COMING UP CAN THIS
MARRIAGE BE SAVED?
NOW YOU CAN VOTE ON THE TRUTH.
>> THANK YOUOU SO MUCH.
>> Vivica: THAT'S NEXT.
No matter how much you clean,
does your house still smell
stuffy?
That's because your home is
filled
with soft surfaces that trap
odors
and release them back into the
room.
So, try Febreze Fabric
Refresher.
Febreze finds odors trapped in
fabrics
and cleans them away as it
dries.
Use Febreze every time you tidy
up
to keep your whole house
smelling fresh air clean.
Fabric Refresher even works for
clothes you want
to wear another day.
Make Febreze part of your clean
routine
for whole home freshness.
(MEG VO)
I can just suck up my
endometriosis pain...
Or I can...
(DIANE VO)
I can keep apologizing...
Or I can...
(SHERRY VO)
I can hope my pain gets better
on its own...
Or I can talk to
my gynecologist today!
(AVO)
You didn't choose to have
endometriosis...
but you can choose to ask
if ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA is specifically
developed for women
with moderate to severe
endometriosis pain.
In clinical trials,
ORILISSA was proven to reduce 3
common types of
endometriosis pain,
painful periods,
pelvic pain in between
periods,
and pain with sex.
Don't use ORILISSA if you are or
may be pregnant,
have osteoporosis,
severe liver disease, or are
taking drugs like
cyclosporine or gemfibrozil.
It may cause abnormal
liver tests.
ORILISSA may change your
periods, making it hard
to know if you are pregnant.
It does not prevent pregnancy.
Use birth control that does not
contain hormones.
ORILISSA may cause suicidal
thoughts or actions.
It may also cause bone loss.
Ask your gynecologist if
ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA. Made for endo pain.
60% of women wear
the wrong size pad
and can experience leaks.
You don't have to.
With Always My Fit,
try the next size up
and get up to 20% better
coverage day or night.
Because better coverage
means better protection.
Always
>> Vivica: WITH DON'S MASSIVE
WEIGHT LOSS CAME MASSIVE
PROBLEMS FOR THEIR MARRIAGE.
JEALOUSY AND NAME CALLING, WITH
ALLEGATIONS OF CHEATING.
AS THE ARGUMENTS INCREASED SO
DID THE DRINKING.
AUDIENCE IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO
TELL THE TRUTH.
CAN THIS MARRIAGE BE SAVED?
PRESS YES OR NO ON YOUR TABLET.
AMERICA, YOU CAN VOTE AT HOME
TOO.
GO TO OUR WEBSITE
FACETHETRUTHTV.COM.
>> Vivica: OKAY.
THE RESULTS ARE IN.
71% SAID YES.
THIS MARRIAGE CAN BE SAVED.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Vivica: DON AND BRANDON,
PLEASE COME JOIN ME IN THE
CIRCLE OF TRUTH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Vivica: OKAY.
HOW DO YOU ALL FEEL HEARING
THOSE RESULTS?
>> I FEEL AWESOME.
I FEEL GREAT ABOUT THAT.
>> Vivica: YES.
>> I THINK IT CAN BE SAVED.
>> Vivica: GOODBYE, I'M GLAD TO
HEAR THAT.
HOW BUT, DARLING?
>> IT'S THE TRUTH.
>> Vivica: YOU WANT TO SAVE THE
MARRIAGE AND THINGS TO CONTINUE.
>> I COULDN'T FIND A BETTER MAN.
>> Vivica: THEY'RE IN LOVE
Y'ALL.
OKAY.
TRUTH TEAM, WHAT SAY YOU.
JUDGE MARY.
>> YOU DID A TOTAL TURN AROUND,
A NEW LIFE.
MAYBE DRAG HIM WITH YOU MORE.
MAYBE YOU NEED TO DO THAT MORE.
RESPECT YOURSELF.
ALWAYS RESPECT YOURSELF.
ARE YOU A MOTHER, THAT'S SO
IMPORTANT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> Vivica: DR. JUDY.
>> DON CAN ONLY TELL YOU SO MANY
TIMES YOU'RE THE LOVE OF HER
LIFE.
YOU HAVE TO KNOW THAT YOURSELF,
AND NO YOU CAN'T KEEP YOUR LOVED
ONES ON A SHORT LEASH.
THE MORE YOU DO THAT THE MORE
YOU PROVOKE THINGS THAT COULD
ANGER AND UPSET YOU FURTHER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> TO HEL HELP YOU GUYS WITH THE
NEWER COMMUNICATION
DIFFICULTIES.
THERE IS A IMBALANCE WITH THE
COMMUNICATION.
WE WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH FREE
MARRIAGE COUNSELING TO
STRENGTHEN YOUR MARRIAGE MORE.
>> Vivica: ROSIE.
>> WE ARE TALKING  ABOUT A
DIFFERENT TRANSFORMATION.
WE GO THROUGH THIS WEIGHT LOSS
AND OUR BODY CHANGES.
THEN WE LOOK IN THE MIRROR AND
SAY I'M NOT HAPPY WITH WHAT I
SEE.
SO WE ARE GIFTS YOU WITH THE
SURGICAL PROCEDURE TO REMOVE THE
EXCESS SKIN.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WOW.
>> THANK YOU, SO MUCH.
>> Vivica: DON AND BRANDON,
THANK YOU FOR HAVING THE COURAGE
TO FACE THE TRUTH.
KNOW WE WISH YOU THE ABSOLUTE
BEST.
>> ALRIGHT.
>> Vivica: IF YOU HAVE A LOVED
ONE STRUGGLING AND YOU WANT THEM
TO "FACE THE TRUTH" JUST VISIT
OUR WEBSITE AT
FACETHETRUTHTV.COM.
>> Vivica: YOU WERE HOMELESS.
>> FOR ABOUT A YEAR.
>> Vivica: WITH A BABY.
>> A FAMILY IN CHRIS IS.
CRISIS.>> YOU CHEATED ON HER.
>> CAN THEY FIND A FIX OR CALL
IT QUITS.
"FACE
♪
Y
The masculine fragrance.
Yves Saint Laurent.
>> Vivica: TODAY ON "FACE THE
TRUTH."
YOU SAID YOU WERE HOMELESS.
>> YES MA'AM FOR ABOUT A YEAR.
>> Vivica: WITH A BABY.
>> WITH A BABY.
>> YOU CHEATED WHEN SHE WAS
PREGNANT.
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT,