[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Hey!
Hey, Rob.
Rob McCann?
- Yes?
♪ ♪
- Victim's Robert McCann.
He took one
to the heart at 10:34.
- Pretty specific time
of death.
- Yeah.
Two citizens heard shots fired
and called 911.
- We don't usually get called
to the party for a shooting.
- This isn't just a shooting.
It's way bigger than that.
Black victim and...
"vermin."
[indistinct radio chatter]
Written in the guy's blood.
We're thinking maybe
we have a hate crime here.
- Yeah, you were right to call
and loop us in.
Any witnesses?
- We're canvassing,
but none so far.
- What about physical evidence?
- It's early days, but we found
a dark blue fiber
transferred
from the killer's shirt.
[indistinct chatter]
- That pin.
Units gave these to
embedded journalists in Iraq.
- He was a reporter.
- That could explain "vermin."
Puts a new spin on this,
doesn't it?
- Yeah, it does.
- Maggie?
- Hey, Paul.
- It's been a while.
Since Jason's--
- Yeah.
My husband used to write
freelance pieces for Paul.
- Special Agent Zidan.
- So Rob McCann.
We're all in a state of shock.
It's such a terrible tragedy.
- How well did you know him?
- Well, I worked with Rob
every day for seven years.
I watched him grow
into one of our star reporters.
- You know if he had
any enemies?
- Well, that's
an understatement.
He wrote exposés for us.
Mostly about public corruption.
He upset a great many people.
Powerful people.
- What about threats?
- We all get 'em.
It's part of the job
these days.
You know, angry calls.
Reader comments, but some
of Rob's were truly vile.
- Any of them more
than just words?
- As a matter of fact, yes.
Two days ago, a man tried
to force his way in here,
demanding to talk to Rob.
- Rob McCann.
Shot dead.
Possibly because
he was a journalist.
These are troubled times
for the Fourth Estate, folks.
Exhibit A.
This guy who crashed "Ledger"
offices to confront McCann.
He bolted before security
could grab him,
but he is described as tall.
40, salt-and-pepper beard.
See if McCann's coworkers
know who he is,
and have your team start
looking into McCann's articles.
Who'd he call out?
Whose toes did he step on?
I want names, people.
JT, where are we on the wife?
- Linda McCann--she was at
a medical conference in L.A.
Flight lands at JFK
in two hours.
- Jubal?
- Yeah?
- I was checking posts
on the "Ledger" website.
I think I found something.
- Besides vitriol?
- I don't know what's wrong
with these people...
especially this guy.
Crusader86 here.
He posted 30 comments
on Rob McCann's articles
in the last two months,
and here is what
he posted yesterday.
- "McCann is vermin,
and he deserves to die."
- He used that same word
in two other posts.
- Can you get me his name?
I'm assuming
it's not crusader86.
- It looks like the account
is tied
to an email registered
to an Edgar Santos.
- Edgar Santos.
That sounds familiar,
because--where is it? Yes.
Santos was a building inspector
who took bribes to look
the other way
on code violations.
Two months ago
McCann wrote that story.
Now Santos is facing
major prison time.
He certainly
matches the description:
tall, 40,
salt-and-pepper beard.
How about that?
- Hi, I'm here with FBI
Special Agent Maggie Bell.
She's radiant
with lustrous hair
and brown eyes that gleam
with sensual promise.
She's clad in a low-cut blouse
which,
in this reporter's view,
is not quite low cut enough.
- [Maggie laughs]
- Oh, boy. Hot and cut.
- What are you watching?
- Nothing.
- Let's go.
- What? We have a lead?
- Better yet.
We have a suspect.
[dramatic music]
- Edgar Santos?
We need to talk.
- What about?
- We want to talk to you about
where you were last night.
- Hey, hey, I didn't give you
permission to do--
- I don't need your permission.
Check this out.
♪ ♪
- The address for
the New York "Ledger"
and Rob McCann's apartment.
- And he got a ticket,
at 10:00 last night,
two blocks from Central Park.
- You know what? I'm not going
anywhere with you people.
It's voluntary questioning,
and I can say no.
- Not anymore.
You're under arrest.
That look familiar?
- Some comments I posted.
So what?
- Calling Rob McCann vermin.
- Hey. Freedom of speech.
- Not when you
threaten his life.
- What about my life, huh?
Look what he did to me
with that article of his.
I lost my job, my wife,
my reputation, my freedom.
I lost everything,
because of him.
- Yeah.
Did he make you
take those bribes too?
- It's not like
I was the only one.
- Right.
This is all his fault
which is why you drove down
to the New York Ledger.
Give him a piece
of your mind, right?
But when that didn't work,
you took it to the next level.
- Not sure what you mean.
- Rob McCann was
murdered last night.
- He's dead?
- You have his home address.
You were stalking him.
- No. I mean I wouldn't say--
- And then you caught up
with him in the park,
and you shot him.
- What? No.
No, it wasn't me.
I swear to you
I did not kill him.
- He was a great reporter.
Happily married.
He had his whole life
ahead of him,
and then
just like that...
snatched away.
- What has she told you
about Jason?
- That he was a reporter
who died in a car crash.
- That's why this case strikes
such a chord in her.
Why she identifies so strongly
with the victim.
- It won't affect her
objectivity as an investigator.
- Well, I trust you'll keep me
in the loop,
if you see that changing.
- This puts you in the area
when Rob McCann died,
so explain that.
- Okay.
I saw McCann catch a cab,
and I followed him,
but I ran a red light
trying to keep up.
That's how I got the ticket.
After that, I drove around
looking for him.
I was about to give up when
I saw him walk into the park.
- And you walked
in right after him.
- No.
I drove around
to Central Park West
and waited for him
to come out the other side.
I just wanted to talk to him,
all right?
But he never showed.
- Okay.
Then give me a witness
that saw you sitting
in your car,
in Central Park West.
- I can't.
There was no witness.
- First degree murder.
Lying in wait.
Do you have any idea
what's about to happen to you?
- Wait.
Wait.
There was somebody.
- Who?
- A jogger.
He came out of the park,
off the path
that I figured McCann was on.
- When was that?
- A little after 10:30 maybe.
- What did he look like?
- Like a jogger.
I don't know.
He was wearing a hoodie.
- What color?
- Dark blue.
- There's your jogger.
No CCTV footage,
but I did manage
to find a restaurant
with security cameras
pointed towards the right
stretch of Central Park West.
The blue fiber came back
as a cotton-poly blend
which is consistent with
the sweatshirt he's wearing,
and there's Santos,
from 10:25 to 10:42.
He never left his car.
- Which alibis him out.
- I'm starting to wonder.
I mean you would expect
a murder like this
to be more rage-filled.
You know, with signs
of a beating
or gunshot wounds to the face.
We have none of that.
- Maybe the killer
saw Santos' post
and left that message
to throw us off?
- I was thinking
the same thing.
In fact, aspects of this
remind me of a case
I was consulting on last year.
- What case?
- The death of a Michigan state
senator, in Lansing.
- I read that.
A mugging gone wrong?
- Well, those were
the official findings,
but this guy had
some really shady dealings,
and I always thought that
the murder was more planned.
- Do you think we're dealing
with the same killer?
- I don't know,
but the senator died
from a single shot
to the heart,
and a jogger was caught
on video fleeing the scene.
- Here's the jogger
from the Michigan case.
- I mean it could be
the same guy.
- Yeah, but he's wearing
a hoodie too.
You can't tell.
- Unless we compare the gaits.
We have a software that can
analyze
the biomechanics
of how he moves.
Your gait can be as unique
as your fingerprint.
91% match.
The Michigan jogger and
the Central Park West jogger--
they're the same person.
- Looks to me like Rob McCann's
murder was a professional hit.
For mild-to-moderate eczema,
EUCRISA can be...
...used almost everywhere on
almost everybody.
Like the arm of an angel.
Or the leg of this little guy.
For ages 2 and up,
prescription EUCRISA works at
and below the surface
of the skin.
It blocks overactive
PDE4 enzymes
which is believed
to reduce inflammation.
And it's steroid-free.
Do not use if you are allergic
to EUCRISA or its ingredients.
Allergic reactions may occur
at or near the application site.
The most common side effect
is application site pain.
Ask your doctor about EUCRISA.
How did we test our
Dixie Ultra plates?
With two pounds of steak.
In each hand.
Dixie Ultra.
Stress tested so you can
stress less at dinner.
Booking a flight
at the last minute
doesn't have to be expensive.
Just go to priceline.
It's the best place
to book a flight
a few days before my trip
and still save up to 40%.
Just tap and go...
For the best savings on flights,
go to priceline.
In terms of treating
sensitivity,
3 days is really fast.
The dentist
is going to be able to provide
that to their patients.
Sensodyne Rapid Relief in my
opinion is a game changer.
It's going to let the dentist
offer their patient
sensitivity relief in 3 days.
It has a formulation
that lays down a barrier of
protection against sensitivity.
Within 3 days, say over the
course of a weekend
you're going to start feeling
significant results.
To say that it works in
3 days really is
a big deal.
- People, please turn
your hymnals
to section 1958
of the federal code
with the snappy title
"Murder for Hire."
We now believe McCann's killer
is a pro
who also took out a state
senator in Lansing last year.
- Quantico's video analysis
indicates that the suspect
is a white male,
30 to 40's, 6" tall.
- Let's call
Lansing area hotels.
Get the names of the guests
that checked out
right after
the senator's murder.
Our guy may be on that list.
- I was doing my residency
at St. Luke's
when Rob was embedded
with the Marines in Fallujah.
That's when I was terrified
I'd lose him.
Not now.
Not here.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
- We're very sorry
for your loss.
- So someone hired
this man to...
Why?
Over something Rob wrote?
- We're not sure yet.
Did he have any issues
with drugs? Gambling?
- No. Nothing like that.
- Has he been worried lately
or concerned?
- If anything, he was excited
about a new story
he was working on.
- What story?
- He wasn't ready to talk
about it yet.
He said it was
the sort of thing
that could win a Pulitzer.
- Most reporters
keep notebooks.
Did your husband have one?
- Yes.
- Is it here?
- He carried it with him.
- It wasn't found on his body.
- Are you sure?
Rob never went anywhere
without his notebook.
That's significant, isn't it?
- It might be.
Do you have any idea why he was
in the park last night?
- I don't know exactly.
When we talked on the phone,
he did say
he was planning
to meet with a source.
- A source on this news story?
- Yes, I think so.
- I talked to Rob's editor
and his colleagues.
He didn't tell them
about the story either.
- Well, whatever it is,
I think it's the key to this.
What does his browser
history show?
- Mostly stuff for articles
he had in the pipeline,
except for some searches
on pediatric oncology.
- Does Rob have a kid
in his circle who has cancer?
- Not that we can find.
- Okay.
What about this source?
Any phone calls that point
to who that might be?
- Rob did get some calls
from a burner phone,
but we're still trying to trace
who it belongs to.
- And Rob McCann's autopsy
report just dropped.
Looks like he had
a 0.07 blood alcohol level.
- Okay, so he met
his source for drinks.
- That is my takeaway.
- Could you put any
of those drinks on a card?
- No.
It looks like he paid cash.
He withdrew $100 from an ATM
on 67th and Columbus.
- Can you shoot us over a list
of all the bars
and restaurants in the area?
- Hold on. I might not need to.
Checking past credit
card charges.
I see two visits to a bar
a block away from that ATM.
- Yeah, I remember him.
He sat right over there.
Ordered two glasses of pinot.
Hey, my shift just ended.
Is this gonna take long?
- It will with that attitude.
Who was he with?
- He was alone.
It seemed like he was waiting
for someone, but nobody showed,
so he paid up and split.
- Anybody come in after
he left?
Maybe looking for him?
- Nope.
There was a guy.
- What guy?
- He was at the bar.
When pinot left,
he left right after him.
- Do you have security cameras?
- Just the one pointed
at the till to keep us honest.
- The guy at the bar.
Have you seen him before?
Maybe a regular?
- Definitely not a regular.
- Why are you so sure?
- He tried to play a song
on the jukebox.
The regulars know
it hasn't worked in months.
- The bad news is there's
no cameras outside the bar,
so we couldn't get eyes
on whoever followed McCann,
but here's the good news:
ERT lifted a primo print
off the jukebox's coin
return button
belonging to one
William Patterson.
- Patterson has a record?
- No.
His prints popped because
he signed up for global entry.
- Could he be our jogger?
- Same age and height.
On the other hand,
he's a math professor at NYU,
so there's that.
He lives in Scarsdale.
I just sent
his address and photo.
- Okay.
Thanks.
Not a lot of hit men out there
who are math professors.
- Which makes it
a pretty great cover.
- Isn't it more likely
that Patterson was the source
that Rob was meeting?
- Then why didn't they
actually meet?
Why didn't he show
his face at the bar?
Why did he follow Rob out?
- So our killer, whoever it is,
just goes up to Rob,
has no idea who he is,
and shoots him.
Cold blood.
Do you think he even thinks
about the pain
he's left behind?
All the dominoes that fall?
The wife he made a widow?
[somber music]
- A thing like that
must be hard.
♪ ♪
- It is.
Really wish you could
have met Jason.
- Me too.
- You guys would have
hit it off.
I would say
one of my favorite
things about Jason is that...
In some small way, he believed
that, being a reporter,
he could change the world.
I think he did.
♪ ♪
[phone rings]
- Jubal.
What you got?
- Hey, there's a flag
on the play.
Forget Patterson's house.
We got a hit on his vehicle.
[dramatic music]
[indistinct chatter]
- Thirty yards,
east southeast there.
Backed up.
The turnoff says a mile
down the road.
- Are you okay?
- Fine.
- Back about another 60 paces.
♪ ♪
[police radio chatter]
- It's Patterson.
Do your asthma symptoms
ever hold you back?
About 50% of people with
severe asthma
have too many cells called
eosinophils in their lungs.
Eosinophils are a key
cause of severe asthma.
FASENRA is designed to target
and remove these cells.
FASENRA is an add-on
injection for people 12
and up with asthma
driven by eosinophils.
FASENRA is not a rescue
medicine
or for other
eosinophilic conditions.
FASENRA is proven to help
prevent severe asthma attacks,
improve breathing, and can
lower oral steroid use.
FASENRA may cause
allergic reactions.
Get help right away if you
have swelling of your
face, mouth, and tongue, or
trouble breathing.
Don't stop your asthma
treatments
unless your doctor
tells you to.
Tell your doctor if you have a
parasitic infection
or your asthma worsens.
Headache and sore throat may
occur.
Haven't you missed enough?
Ask an asthma specialist
about FASENRA.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may
be able to help.
Our craftsmen begin each day...
...Perfectly seasoning our
Hillshire Farm smoked sausage.
So by simply adding
the right ingredients...
...You can end each day crafting
a perfectly delicious dinner.
(WOMAN)
What should we do with it first?
(MAN)
Road trip.
(WOMAN)
Yes.
Off-road trip.
(COUPLE)
[LAUGHTER]
(COUPLE VO)
Whoa!
(MAN)
How hot is the diablo chili?
(WAITRESS)
Well. You've got to sign a
waiver.
[LAUGHTER]
(RANGER)
You folks need bear repellent?
(WOMAN)
Ah, we're good.
(MAN)
Yes.
(VO)
It's a big world.
Our new Forester just made it
even bigger.
(WOMAN)
So what should we do second?
(VO)
The 2019 Subaru Forester.
The most adventurous Forester
ever.
Every year,
Team Rubicon enlists the help
of veterans to provide relief
to communities
affected by natural disasters.
Do it for those
who need your help.
Mountain Dew
is proud
to support
the efforts
of
Team Rubicon.
Let's Do.
♪
Raquen...
Rakutahn...
Rakooten...
♪
Rakuten
Oh!
Is this my money?
Whoaaah!
Haha!
Rakuten
♪
Ahhh!
Rakuten!
- Looks like Patterson
was going about 80
when the driver's side front
tire blew, and he lost control.
- Which is in keeping with the
man's abysmal driving record.
Five wrecks in two years.
- Doesn't exactly
fit the profile
for your methodical hit man.
- Well, that's because
he isn't one.
Apparently, Patterson tore his
Achilles tendon six weeks ago.
- So he couldn't be our jogger.
What else do we know about him?
- Not enough.
He's not married.
No kids.
No family we can find.
- But we do know he spoke
to Rob McCann.
Those burner calls
that Rob got?
We traced 'em to a phone
Patterson purchased last week.
- Okay.
Thanks.
- So Patterson is
definitely Rob's source,
but what's the story?
- Something sensitive enough
that he bought a burner phone.
- He took some
major precautions here.
That's why he tailed Rob
out of the bar,
so they could talk in private.
- Yeah, he was afraid
someone might find out
he met with a reporter.
- So now he's dead
in a car crash?
- I know.
The timing's weird.
- Agent Bell, Agent Zidan.
It's part of
a radio-controlled receiver
used to detonate a small IED
that blew the tire.
This was no accident.
- I bet whoever killed Rob
also killed Patterson.
- The hit man had to be tailing
him to detonate the IED.
- Yeah.
Make sure the target was dead.
- Country road.
No traffic.
It's the perfect place
to pull this off.
It could explain
why Patterson was speeding.
The hit man was chasing him.
- Suspect might have touched
this vehicle.
I want to get it
checked for prints.
Driver's side door.
All around the body.
- Got it.
- Wait.
Where are the keys?
There's no key in the ignition.
- Maybe the hit man took 'em.
I bet he's headed
to Patterson's house.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
Clear.
- Clear.
- Clearly our hit man
beat us here.
- First, he takes
Rob's notebook.
Then he tears this place apart.
This guy's tying up loose ends.
- But what's he looking for?
- I don't know,
but whatever it is
might still be here.
I'm gonna call T
and have him run a search.
- Hey, check this out.
It's Patterson's ER paperwork
for when he tore his Achilles.
- So?
- So we need to find people
who knew him, right?
Lists his emergency contact.
- Russell Donovan.
- I can't even begin
to process this.
- Mr. Donovan, what was your
relationship to Mr. Patterson?
- William and I met at Yale.
He was my first love.
It didn't last,
but we stayed close.
I think I was one of
the few friends he had.
- When was the last time
you two spoke?
- Three or four days ago
it must have been.
It was a strange call.
- Strange how?
- He was being paranoid.
Saying that he thought people
were following him.
- What people?
- I don't know.
He was eccentric.
I thought he was just being
William, so I humored him.
He was trying to tell me
something, and I didn't listen.
- What else was he involved in,
besides teaching math?
- Statistical analysis.
William was sought after
for his ability
to parse huge sets of data.
It was all a bit over my head.
- "Sought after"?
By whom?
- I know that he was working on
at least one research project.
- Do you know
what the project was?
- No, he didn't tell me.
He was very tight-lipped.
- Okay.
Thank you for your time.
You'll be hearing from us.
That was the head
of NYU's math department.
Patterson's project was funded
by a grant
from the Defense Department.
- Which project?
- It's classified.
- A hit man?
Classified projects?
What the hell is going on here?
[phone chimes]
- I don't know,
but we're gonna need
a warrant
to check out that research.
- We just got a lead
on his murder.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, watch and learn, kids.
This is yeoman's work
by young Kristen here.
Or yeo-woman's.
♪ ♪
- Drone?
Car crash?
The killer used a drone
to kill Patterson?
- Yes, but not in the way
that you're thinking.
Remember that
remote-controlled receiver
that blew the tire out?
- Yeah.
- Our killer repurposed it
from a Bluehawk 2 quad copter,
so our techs traced
the serial number
and tracked
the purchase to him.
He paid cash,
so no digital trail.
- Damn.
Still can't see his face.
- 'Cause he's staying
turned away from the camera.
This guy's good.
- Wait, what's on his neck?
Is that a scar?
- AFIS logs scars and tattoos.
Did you run it
through the system?
- Nice, but she found
a better way,
by going back
to the senator's murder.
- These are all the people
who checked out of
Lansing hotels the day
after the senator's death.
I filtered through
for white males 30 to 40,
6" tall,
staying alone,
which narrowed it
down to 200 people,
but only one of them booked
a ticket to New York
in the past week.
Frank Cutler.
♪ ♪
- That's him.
Same scar on the neck.
- Good work, Kristen.
Let's put out a wide BOLO
for Frank Cutler.
- It's a little too early
for a victory lap,
but at least
now we have a face.
♪ ♪
What?
Maggie, you recognize him?
- No.
Excuse me.
♪ ♪
- This is Jason Bell
reporting live.
- You're the biggest nerd.
- Hot and cut.
♪ ♪
♪
♪ And everywhere I go ♪
♪ There's always
something to remind me ♪
♪ Of another
place and time ♪
♪
♪ Of another
place and time ♪
♪No one will love you...
...like I do♪
♪
♪No one will hold you...
...like I do♪
Dare to be Devoted.
Jared®.
♪
Dare to Stop Searching,
with Jared's unparalleled
selection of diamonds...
and price match guarantee.
Dare to be Devoted.
Only at Jared®.
s
before she puts them in the
dishwasher.
So what does the dishwasher do?
(VO) Cascade Platinum does the
work for you.
Prewashing and removing
stuck-on foods, the first time.
(Mom) Wow! That's clean!
(VO) Cascade Platinum.
I AM TOTALLY BLIND.
AND NON-24 CAN MAKE ME SHOW UP
TOO EARLY... OR TOO LATE.
OR MAKE ME FEEL LIKE
I'M NOT REALLY "THERE."
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR,
AND CALL
844-234-2424.
At Booking.com,
we can't guarantee
you'll find gold
on your wild west vacation...
But we can guarantee
the best price
on that thar rental cabin
or any hotel,
home,
boat,
yurt,
whatever.
♪
Just don't get
carried away
with the
wild west thing.
Hey guys.
Get the best price
on homes, hotels
and so much more.
Booking.com, Booking.yeah
- Hey.
What's going on?
Is that a picture
of Frank Cutler?
- No. It's nothing.
- Maggie?
Maggie, what's up?
- Look.
The day that I lost Jason,
we were having lunch together,
and I took this video of him.
I don't know how many times
I've watched this, but...
Is that Frank Cutler?
[suspenseful music]
- I mean the hat's similar,
but there's no scar
on his neck.
- Yeah, but that's
just because of the angle.
OA, it's him.
- I'm not so sure.
Besides, your husband died
in a car crash.
- So?
We thought Patterson did too.
- You said that
he was broadsided.
That the other driver
went through a light,
so what are you saying?
- Okay. I'm saying that
that's the day Jason died,
and Frank Cutler
is right there staring at him.
- If that's even him.
Let me ask you this.
Was there any sign
of foul play with Jason?
Any indication
that someone was after him?
One time,
I got detained by TSA,
because some guy
on the terror list
had my name and looked enough
like me to be my brother.
This stuff happens
all the time.
- Yeah, no, I get that,
but what if this
really is Cutler?
- I mean he's just walking down
the street.
Look, Maggie, I can't imagine
what you've been through.
When you lose a loved one,
it's human nature
to look for answers.
For a reason why.
But sometimes--
- All right, listen.
I just asked you if you thought
it was Frank Cutler.
Okay?
That's all I wanted to know.
- Agent Bell. We searched
the Patterson house.
Nothing much stood out,
except for this.
- Thank you.
He rented a safe deposit box.
The First Central Savings Bank.
That was a week ago.
- Maybe whatever
he put in there
the killer was searching for.
- All right.
Let's go check it out.
- Maggie, may I have a moment?
I'm a profiler.
I read people.
Is there anything
I need to know?
- No, ma'am.
- I ask because a personal bias
can affect one's instincts.
Make an investigator
move forward too soon
or move away too late.
- I'm right where I need to be
on this one.
- You should know that
Frank Cutler
is a fake identity,
but the trail of bodies
he's left is very real.
- He's killed other people?
- So far we've found
nine suspected
contract killings in six states
where Cutler just happened
to be in the area.
We're taking a fresh look
at all those cases,
including the killing
of that state senator.
I know you want to take
this man down, Maggie,
but he is lethally dangerous.
If you find out where he is,
I need you to call in SWAT.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- All that's missing
is a drum roll.
I don't know what I was
expecting, but it wasn't that.
- There's no imprint on them,
so not pharmaceutical.
- Street drugs?
Why rent a box to stash those?
- Well, maybe it'll make more
sense once the lab IDs them.
- I'm sorry,
but I have a situation.
Mr. Patterson's here.
- What?
- He wants access to his box.
He has proper ID, so--
- Can I see that?
- What should I tell him?
- You're not gonna
tell him anything.
How many customers
are in the bank right now?
- We were closing.
Mr. Patterson
and the two of you.
- What about employees?
- Six, including me,
plus the security guard.
What's going on?
- I know Dana said
to call in SWAT,
but it's gonna take 'em
forever to get here.
- Did you say SWAT?
- If she's gone too long,
he's gonna start
getting suspiciou.
- You're gonna stay here.
Do not leave.
We're gonna go up there.
Try not
to look like feds.
- Excuse me.
[laughs]
- We're not gonna ask
your mother for money now.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Frank Cutler, freeze.
FBI.
Don't move.
- Get down.
Take cover!
You too.
Down!
Take cover!
- Slowly put your hands
in the air.
Put your hands in the air,
and get down on your knees,
on the ground.
Now.
- Don't turn around.
Do not turn around!
Get on your knees.
- Get down on your knees,
on the ground,
or I will shoot you.
Someone call 911.
Get an ambulance here
immediately.
♪
At Walgreens,
We want you,
to keep doing you...
And we'll take care
of Medicare Part D.
By helping you save up to
$5 on each prescription...
So you can get back to
doing the things you love.
Stop in and start saving
on your Medicare Part D
prescriptions today...
Walgreens.
Trusted since 1901.
♪ I FEEL MOST TIMES
WE'RE HIGH AND LOW ♪
♪ HIGH AND LOW ♪
♪ IF I HAD MY WAY ♪
ENHANCE YOUR MOMENTS.
SAN PELLEGRINO.
TASTEFULLY ITALIAN.
New Whole Blends Ginger
Recovery.
Blended with purpose, for
fragile hair.
SAN PELLEGRINO.
With revitalizing ginger, known
to recover strength,
and golden honey.
As a whole blend,
it provides twice the breakage
protection.
To make hair stronger instantly.
Blended makes us better.
Whole Blends.
By Garnier, naturally.
I Hear it in the Background and
she's Watching too, saying
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
♪
[FRIEND]
I've never seen that before.
♪
I have...
[sirens wailing]
- If Cutler dies,
the truth about the case--
everything he's done--
dies with him.
- Maybe not.
Look what I found
in his jacket pocket.
Right now, the car's
the best lead we got.
- Yeah, and hopefully
those pills.
- In spite of the rather
rushed timeframe,
I was able to identify
the pill's active ingredient
as a variant of cytarabine
which is an anti-metabolite.
- Very impressive.
Care to translate it for me?
- Yeah.
It's a hot new cancer drug.
Just came out.
- If the pills
are a cancer drug,
so then why no name
or brand imprint?
FDA requires that.
- Hmm, well, that's only once
it's been made available
to the public.
- Okay, so maybe these ones
are for testing or drug trials?
- Yeah, could be.
Whoa.
- What? What is it?
- The results on the pill's
inactive ingredients.
Something is way off.
[dramatic music]
- Hey, OA.
I got something.
Found it under the seat.
♪ ♪
- Rob McCann.
The missing notebook.
- Yeah,
well, there's a problem.
♪ ♪
- Looks like some kind of code.
- A lot of reporters use
their own shorthand.
Jason did the same thing.
- You can't read it?
- There's no way.
Hey, Kristen.
What's up?
- So the pills you guys found?
It's Lucasil.
It's a recently approved drug
for treating
childhood leukemia.
- Why would Patterson
have those?
- I don't know,
but it explains
why Rob was researching
pediatric oncology.
- Yeah, especially if there
were problems with the drug.
The pills?
They show impurities.
Like, serious ones.
- Who makes Lucasil?
- Morrowick Medical.
In fact, the drug put them
on the map.
They just went public
with a huge IPO.
- Okay. Look into Morrowick.
Let us know what you find out.
- On it.
- You thinking what
I'm thinking?
- Morrowick had issues
with Lucasil.
Rob was gonna tell the world.
- And bring down the company,
so somebody
hired Cutler to stop him,
and the evidence might be
in this notebook.
We just can't read it.
- Maybe Rob's wife can.
- It's been a while,
but some of this
is coming back now.
- What does it say?
- These are Rob's notes
from an intervew with someone.
No name.
Just an initial: Q.
- Q.
Who the hell's Q?
- In Jason's notes, he used
to manipulate the alphabet.
- What if we shift the letters
back by one character?
- Okay, so Q is really P,
for Patterson?
- Okay.
- Looks like this Patterson
is talking about a drug.
Initial M.
- L? Lucasil.
- He's telling Rob
about a factory in China,
I think, that made
a batch of tainted pills.
They found the mistake,
but the pills had already
been distributed
to patients in drug trials.
- Does Patterson say
how he knew about this?
- Here it is.
A major shareholder hired him,
secretly, to run data
to see if patients
had been affected.
- Were they?
- He found a 29%
rise in mortality.
- Wow.
[tense music]
- And the company
kept it quiet.
- Yep.
- He wanted to go public,
to make sure no one else
took the tainted drugs,
but the shareholder refused
and threatened him,
so he reached out to Rob.
Rob was gonna expose this,
wasn't he?
This was his story.
- In his way, he was gonna
change the world.
Does it mention anything about
who the shareholder was?
- It's just initials again.
S.E.
- Which is really R.D.
We know who that is.
Patterson's friend.
♪ ♪
- Russell Donovan
of Donovan Partners.
The VC firm that invested
big in Morrowick Medical.
We hit his home and office,
but he's in the wind.
Now, a little context here.
Not only did Donovan
hire Cutler,
but he also gave meds
to cancer patients
without bothering to mention
they were contaminated.
Let's lean on his family,
his colleagues.
Let's issue
another round of BOLOs.
Let's find this dirt bag.
- Hey.
- Tell me you have
a 20 on Donovan.
- I might: I just found
a satellite office in Brooklyn
where Donovan
parks his chopper.
Pilot just filed a flight plan
for Montreal.
- He's making a run
for the border.
♪ ♪
- Russell Donovan,
we need a few words.
- I've done nothing wrong.
- Really?
What about the tainted pills
in the cancer trials?
- There's no proof of that.
- We have Rob McCann's
notebook.
That has the whole story.
- And we have two payments of
100 grand to Frank Cutler
that we tracked back to you.
- You can direct any further
questions to my attorney.
- Russell Donovan,
you're under arrest.
- Good work out there today.
- I'm sorry.
I know you said
to call in SWAT,
but I was worried that
we would have lost Cutler.
- Well, we might
lose him anyway.
He's out of surgery,
but it's touch-and-go.
You faced down
a monster today, Maggie.
A case a little too
close to home.
How are you?
- I'm fine.
- I used to think that things
would never catch up to me.
I don't want to see you
make the same mistake.
This woman helped me
through things.
She can help you too.
- Thanks.
- Hey.
- Um, listen, so I've been
looking into Cutler.
That's definitely him
in your video.
He was in New York.
- Maybe it's what you said.
He was just walking by.
- Yeah.
That's what I thought too.
But then I looked
into his financials
and a wire transfer
for 100 grand
hit his account
the day Jason died.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
You were right.
Maggie, he was involved.
♪ ♪
[music intensifies]
- I'm sorry.
You can't be in here.
This man is critically ill.
- I need the room.
Get out.
Cutler, wake up.
You remember me?
Not just from the bank
though, right?
- [wheezing]
- Last year. I was sitting
at a café on Amsterdam.
I was with my husband.
Jason.
I was sitting there with Jason.
That's you.
Isn't it?
You killed my husband.
Why did you do it?
Look at me.
- [straining]
- Why did you kill my husband?
Do you even understand
what you took from me?
The life that we were
going to have?
Who hired you?
Do one decent thing right now,
and tell me who hired you.
Please.
Please tell me.
Tell me.
Cutler.
[machines beeping]
[machine flatlining]
- I'm sorry. You need to leave.
- What's happening?
- His BP's cratering.
Vessel may have opened up.
Let's run a CT angio,
and prep the OR.
- Where are you going?
- Back into surgery.
If we're lucky,
we can save his life.
- Where's the OR doctor
on call?
- Dr. Denton!
- I'm right here.
- Page Denton.
- [shaky breathing]
I keep thinking about
how Jason wanted to have kids.
I was the one
that wanted to wait.
I was worried about my career
or whatever.
I just wish I'd have taken
that leap, you know?
Then maybe part of him
would still be with me.
Or if I was at home pregnant,
he wouldn't have been
on the road that night.
- What happened to him
is not on you.
- How did I not see
that it wasn't an accident?
- How could you?
No one else did.
- I'm an FBI agent.
I should have seen the signs.
- Not if there weren't any.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- OA, I think
I've been too afraid to look.
To really face that he's gone.
Did you know that I still have
all of his clothes
in his closet?
I just don't open the door.
- Wherever this goes...
I'm with you.
♪ ♪
- Agent Bell?
I'm sorry, but Mr. Cutler
didn't make it.
♪ ♪
- Stay tuned for scenes
from our next episode.
♪ Que será, será ♪
♪ Whatever will be, will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que será, será ♪
♪ What will be, will be ♪
♪ Whatever will be, will be ♪
♪ Que será, seráaaaaa ♪
Chili's 3 for $10 presents
our signature
sirloin steak.
Aged to perfection
and served with
a starter and drink
for just $10.
Dinner with mom, dad,
grandma and her friend Randy,
who seems to be a little more
than a friend.
Together We Chili's.
As a fitness junkie,
I customize everything -
bike, wheels, saddle.
That's why I switched to
Liberty Mutual.
They customized my insurance, so
I only pay for what I need.
I insured my car,
and my bike.
My calves are custom too,
but I can't insure those...
which is a crying shame.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
Yes, we are twins.
When I went on to Ancestry,
I just put in the name
of my parents and
my grandparents.
I was getting
all these leaves
and I was going back
generation after generation.
You start to see
documents and you see
signatures of
people that you've never met.
I mean, you don't
know these people,
but you feel
like you do.
You get connected
to them.
I wish that I could
get into a time machine
and go back
100 years, 200 years
and just meet
these people.
Being on Ancestry
just made me feel
like I belonged
somewhere.
Discover your story.
Start searching for
free now at Ancestry.com.
Cologuard:
colon cancer screening
for people 50 and
older at average risk.
I'm here for an important
reason. Colon cancer screening.
There's a bunch of places where
screening wouldn't be easy.
Like here.
Or here.
Nope!
But here's a place you can
screen for colon cancer anytime.
With Cologuard.
In private.
Without any special prep.
There really is no place...
like home.
Cologuard is not
right for everyone,
so ask your doctor
if it's right for you.
Why shop Marshalls?
Because...
Their prices will thrill you.
Whoo-hoo!
The brands will surprise you.
Mwah!
And every trip feels
like an instant victory.
Woman:
Marshalls.
Never boring.
Always surprising.
Woman:
Marshalls.