THEY WEREN'T
WEALTHY LANDOWNERS,
THEY DIDN'T HAVE PROPERTIES
OR ANYTHING AT STAKE IN CUBA,
AND THEY HAD AN OPPORTUNITY TO
GO JUST AN HOUR NORTH AND THEN
GET A BETTER LIFE UH, FOR
THEMSELVES AND THEIR FAMILY,
VERY TYPICAL THING THAT
DREW PEOPLE HERE FOREVER.
GATES: THAT'S A BIG
HOUR THOUGH, MAN.
RUBIO: IT IS.
IT'S A BIG JUMP AND I'M
SURE THOSE EARLY YEARS WERE,
WERE DIFFICULT FOR THEM.
GATES: MARCO'S PARENTS
STRUGGLED MIGHTILY TO MAKE IT
IN AMERICA, MOVING FROM NEW
YORK TO MIAMI TO LAS VEGAS,
WORKING IN CASINOS AND HOTELS.
IT WAS AN IMMENSE EFFORT.
BUT EVEN SO, THE COUPLE TOOK
GREAT CARE TO MAKE SURE THAT
THEIR CHILDREN DIDN'T
SEE THEIR EXPERIENCE
AS A LIABILITY.
RUBIO: I NEVER REMEMBER
GROWING UP FEELING LIKE
I WAS LIMITED BECAUSE MY
DAD WAS A BARTENDER AND
MY MOM WORKED AS A MAID
AT THE IMPERIAL PALACE.
SOMEHOW THEY WERE ABLE TO
INSTILL IN US THE BELIEF THAT
THERE WAS NOBODY WE
SAW ON TELEVISION THAT
WE COULDN'T BE ONE DAY.
GATES: THAT'S FABULOUS.
MY PARENTS WERE THE SAME WAY.
THERE WAS NOTHING THAT
WE COULD ASPIRE TO THAT
WE COULD NOT ACHIEVE.
RUBIO: YEAH.
GATES: NOTHING.
RUBIO: THAT'S A REAL GIFT.
GATES: BUT WHERE DO YOU THINK
IT CAME FROM IN YOUR CASE?
RUBIO: I DON'T KNOW, UM.
GATES: I MEAN IT'S KINDA
CRAZY WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
RUBIO: WELL I THINK IT WAS
JUST KIND OF THE POINT OF
MY PARENTS' LIFE.
THEY TRIED A LOT OF
DIFFERENT THINGS,
AND I THINK THEIR FEELING WAS
WE WOULD HAVE THE CHANCE TO DO
THINGS THEY NEVER
HAD A CHANCE TO DO,
BUT INTERESTINGLY ENOUGH,
THEY NEVER HAD A SPECIFIC
DREAM FOR US, THEY JUST
WANTED US TO HAVE A DREAM,
WHATEVER THAT WAS,
AND KINDA PURSUE IT.
GATES: MARCO, OF COURSE,
DID INDEED FIND HIS OWN
DREAMS TO PURSUE.
AFTER GRADUATING FROM THE
UNIVERSITY OF MIAMI LAW SCHOOL,
HE ENTERED POLITICS,
RISING TO BECOME
ONE OF ONLY A HANDFUL OF
LATINOS IN THE U.S. SENATE.
LOOKING BACK, HE REMAINS
INTENSELY GRATEFUL TO HIS
PARENTS, AND SEES HIS SUCCESS
AS A VALIDATION OF THE CHOICE
THEY MADE IN IMMIGRATING,
AND OF THE NATION THEY
CHOSE AS THEIR NEW HOME.
RUBIO: AMERICA IS THIS ONE
PLACE WHERE YOU SAID TO PEOPLE
ALL OVER THE WORLD UH, MAYBE
YOU LIVE SOMEWHERE WHERE THEY
WON'T LET YOU BE WHO YOU
KNOW YOU CAN BE BECAUSE
YOUR FAMILY ISN'T
THE RIGHT PEOPLE.
BUT HERE IT DOESN'T MATTER,
HERE WE'RE GONNA JUDGE YOU BY
HOW HARD YOU'RE WILLING TO
WORK NOT ON WHAT YOUR LAST
NAME IS OR WHERE, WHAT
YOUR GREAT-GRANDFATHER DID.
GATES: MY THIRD GUEST IS
HAWAIIAN CONGRESSWOMAN
TULSI GABBARD.
GABBARD: ALOHA.
GATES: A RISING STAR
ON THE NATIONAL STAGE.
TULSI COMES FROM A
MILITARY FAMILY,
AND FOLLOWED THAT
SAME PATH HERSELF.
SHE JOINED THE ARMY
NATIONAL GUARD IN 2003,
WHEN SHE WAS 22 YEARS OLD.
THE NEXT YEAR, THE MAJORITY
OF HER UNIT WAS SELECTED FOR
SERVICE IN IRAQ,
BUT TULSI WASN'T,
SO SHE MADE A BOLD DECISION.
GABBARD: I KNEW VERY QUICKLY
THAT THERE WAS NO WAY THAT I
COULD STAY BACK IN
BEAUTIFUL HAWAII AS YOU KNOW,
MY FRIENDS AND BROTHERS AND
SISTERS IN UNIFORM DEPLOYED.
GATES: SO YOU VOLUNTEERED.
GABBARD: SO I VOLUNTEERED.
I CALLED MY
COMMANDER AND I TOLD HIM.
I HAVE TO GO WITH YOU GUYS.
AND, AND HE SAID,
NO, YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
AND IT TOOK A FEW
CONVERSATIONS FOR ME TO GET
HIM TO UNDERSTAND THAT I
WAS NOT GOING TO STAY HOME.
GATES: TULSI WAS SENT TO
A BASE IN IRAQ NICKNAMED
"MORTARITAVILLE" DUE TO
FREQUENT ENEMY ATTACKS.
SHE SERVED IN A
FIELD MEDICAL UNIT,
OBSERVING CASUALTIES AND
INJURIES ON A NEAR DAILY
BASIS, CONFRONTING FIRSTHAND
THE REALITIES OF WAR.
GABBARD: IT REALLY SHOWS YOU
WHAT'S IMPORTANT IN LIFE AND,
UM, THE SMALL
THINGS FALL AWAY.
GATES: YEAH.
GABBARD: WE HAD A BIG SIGN IN
OUR CAMP RIGHT ON ONE OF THE
GATES WHERE THE
PATROLS WENT IN AND OUT,
BIG BLACK LETTERS.
IT SAID: "IS TODAY THE DAY?"
GATES: WOW.
GABBARD: AND IT WAS AN
EVER-PRESENT REMINDER OF HOW
FRAGILE LIFE IS AND THAT OUR
TIME COULD COME AT ANY MOMENT,
SO MAKE IT COUNT.
DON'T TAKE
ANYTHING FOR GRANTED.
GATES: TULSI TOLD ME THAT HER
SERVICE WAS A MAJOR MOTIVATION
IN HER DECISION TO
RUN FOR CONGRESS,
DRIVING HER TO RECONSIDER
AMERICA'S MILITARY POLICIES
IN TERMS OF THEIR IMPACT
ON SOLDIERS AND CIVILIANS.
GABBARD: WHAT WILL
THE COST OF THIS BE,
DEVASTATION TO THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE,
TO THE WORLD, AND
WHAT, FOR WHAT?
GATES: A NOTION THAT TRULY HIT
HOME WHEN SHE RETURNED TO HER
FAMILY, AND SAW HOW POWERFULLY
HER ABSENCE HAD AFFECTED THEM.
GABBARD: WHEN I CAME HOME
FROM MY FIRST DEPLOYMENT.
WE PROBABLY LANDED AT
3 OR 4 IN THE MORNING.
WE SAW THE SUN RISING AS
WE WERE MARCHING INTO UM,
THIS HUGE HANGAR WHERE
ALL OF OUR FAMILIES
WERE GATHERED.
AND AS SOON AS THE GENERAL
SAID THAT WE WERE DISMISSED,
UH I RAN TO MY FAMILY AND MY
DAD WAS THE FIRST ONE THAT I
HUGGED AND UM, HE WAS SOBBING.
I DIDN'T, I DIDN'T
KNOW HOW, YOU KNOW,
I WAS SO FOCUSED IN MY WORLD
AND WHAT I WAS DOING I DIDN'T
FULLY REALIZE UNTIL THAT
MOMENT HOW ANXIOUS AND
STRESSED AND
WORRIED THEY WERE.
GATES: AFTER SPENDING
TIME WITH MY GUESTS,
I WAS STRUCK THAT
EACH HAD BEEN MOLDED
AND MOTIVATED BY ADVERSITY.
AS I DUG INTO THEIR ROOTS, I
FOUND THAT THEIR FAMILY TREES
WERE FILLED WITH PEOPLE
WHO SHARED THAT TRAIT.
BUT THEIR STORIES HAD
LARGELY BEEN FORGOTTEN.
IT WAS TIME TO UNEARTH THEM.
I STARTED WITH PAUL RYAN.
AS HIS NAME SUGGESTS, HIS
FATHER'S FAMILY IS IRISH,
AND PAUL IS WELL-VERSED
IN THEIR EXPERIENCE.
HE'S EVEN VISITED THE
TOWNS IN IRELAND WHERE
THE RYANS ONCE LIVED.
HIS MOTHER'S ROOTS, HOWEVER,
ARE A DIFFERENT MATTER.
HE KNOWS THAT SOME OF
HER ANCESTORS WERE GERMAN,
BUT LITTLE MORE.
SO WE BEGAN WITH HIS
MATERNAL GRANDFATHER,
WHOM PAUL LOVED, AND WHOSE
NAME WAS PARTICULARLY GERMAN.
THAT'S DR. ADOLPH HUTTER.
RYAN: MHMM. CAN YOU IMAGINE
HIS NAME WAS ADOLPH HUTTER?
GATES: I KNOW.
WOW. THAT'S...
RYAN: HE WAS IN THE US
NAVY IN WORLD WAR II.
GATES: THAT'S TOUGH.
RYAN: YEAH.
GATES: AND YOU'VE WRITTEN
THAT GROWING UP YOUR
GREATEST ASPIRATION WAS TO
BE LIKE DR. ADOLPH HUTTER.
RYAN: YEAH.
GATES: TELL ME ABOUT THAT.
RYAN: I ADORED THE MAN.
UGH, HE, HE, LIKE MY MOM,
HE WAS A REALLY CHIPPER,
HAPPY, FUNNY GUY,
VERY SMART, UM, WARM.
PEOPLE LIKED
BEING AROUND HIM, UM,
I JUST ADORED HIM.
GATES: PAUL HAD BEEN
TOLD BY HIS RELATIVES
THAT THE HUTTER FAMILY
ORIGINALLY IMMIGRATED TO
THE UNITED STATES
FROM BAVARIA.
BUT HE DIDN'T
KNOW WHEN THEY CAME,
OR ANYTHING AT ALL ABOUT
THE DETAILS OF THEIR JOURNEY.
WE FOUND THE
ANSWERS IN A PAMPHLET,
WRITTEN BUT NEVER PUBLISHED
BY ADOLPH'S GRANDFATHER,
A MAN NAMED JOSEPH HUTTER.
RYAN: "I WAS BORN JUNE 17,
1848 IN GERMANY AND IN 1854
WE CAME TO AMERICA.
I HAD NO IDEA THEY
CAME THAT EARLY.
IN 1854, WE CAME TO AMERICA
STOPPING AT HAVERSTRAW,
NEW YORK STATE UNTIL 1855."
GATES: HAVERSTRAW IS
ABOUT 40 MILES NORTH OF
NEW YORK CITY, BY THE WAY.
RYAN: OH OKAY.
NEVER HEARD OF IT.
"WE TRAVELED BY
RAIL TO MILWAUKEE.
WE WERE PENNILESS, AND
IN ORDER TO CONTINUE OUR
TRAVEL TO MADISON BY RAIL,
WE HAD TO PLEDGE ALL OF
OUR PERSONAL BELONGINGS,
SUCH AS BEDDING, ETCETERA,
FOR WHICH WE RECEIVED $12,
AND THIS TOOK US TO
MADISON, WISCONSIN."
THAT'S AN IMMIGRANT
STORY IF THERE EVER WAS ONE.
MAN, THAT'S A GREAT STORY.
I LOVE THAT STORY.
GATES: HAPPILY FOR PAUL,
HIS ANCESTOR'S STORY WAS
ABOUT TO GET EVEN BETTER.
ACCORDING TO JOSEPH, THE
HUTTERS CAME TO WISCONSIN TO
SETTLE IN SAUK COUNTY, WHERE
THERE WAS A GROWING COMMUNITY
OF GERMAN IMMIGRANTS.
BUT BY THE TIME
THEY REACHED MADISON,
THEY WERE
PENNILESS ONCE AGAIN,
AND SAUK COUNTY WAS
OVER 50 MILES AWAY!
THEY HAD NOTHING LEFT TO
SELL, SO THEY CONTINUED
THEIR JOURNEY, ON FOOT.
JOSEPH WAS ONLY SIX
YEARS OLD AT THE TIME.
RYAN: THEY WALKED 50 MILES.
GATES: YEAH 50 MILES.
THEY HAD NO MONEY.
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
RYAN: NO.
GATES: AND IF WE DO THE MATH,
JOSEPH'S MOTHER WAS LIKELY
PREGNANT WHEN THE FAMILY
IMMIGRATED AND WHEN THE FAMILY
WAS MAKING THAT 50
MILE WALK TO SAUK COUNTY.
CAN YOU IMAGINE THAT?
TALK ABOUT TOUGH.
RYAN: WOW, WOW.
PREGNANT WALKING 50 MILES
TO PLAIN, WISCONSIN
FROM MADISON.
IT'S A PRETTY HILLY AREA TOO.
I KNOW THAT SPOT. WOW.
GATES: WE NOW
TURNED TO THE ARCHIVES,
TO COMPARE JOSEPH'S ACCOUNT
WITH THE HISTORICAL RECORD.
THE 1860 CENSUS SHOWED JOSEPH
AS AN 11-YEAR-OLD BOY LIVING
ON THE SOUTH EDGE OF SAUK
COUNTY WITH HIS PARENTS:
JOHN AND BARBARA HUTTER.
THEY ARE YOUR THIRD
GREAT-GRANDPARENTS.
RYAN: DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THAT.
DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THEIR NAMES.
WOW. THAT'S REALLY SOMETHING.
GATES: NOW I'M GOING TO SHOW
YOU SOMETHING REALLY COOL.
COULD YOU PLEASE
TURN THE PAGE?
RYAN: ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
GATES: SOMETHING YOU
NEVER DREAMED YOU'D SEE
IN YOUR WHOLE LIFE.
PAUL, YOU'RE LOOKING
AT THE PASSENGER LIST,
RYAN: OH REALLY?
GATES: FOR A SHIP
CALLED THE "CAESAR",
IT ARRIVED AT THE PORT OF
NEW YORK ON JUNE 20, 1854.
RYAN: HOW THE HECK.
HOW DO YOU GUYS
GET THIS STUFF?
HOW DO YOU DO THAT?
GATES: WOULD YOU PLEASE
READ WHO WAS ON THAT SHIP.
RYAN: THERE YOU
HAVE IT RIGHT THERE.
"JOHANNES HUTTER, 42,
FARMER, BARBARA, 42,
MICHAEL, 9, JOSEPH, 5."
GATES: YOU ARE LOOKING AT
THE RECORD OF THE MOMENT
THAT YOUR ANCESTORS
FIRST STEPPED FOOT IN
THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA.
RYAN: WOW. WOW.
THE "CAESAR"
PASSENGER MANIFEST.
GATES: MM-HMM.
RYAN: THAT'S AMAZING.
GATES: THE HUTTERS ARRIVED IN
AMERICA WITH NO MONEY AND NO
CONNECTIONS, AND FOUND
THEMSELVES NEAR THE BOTTOM
OF THE ECONOMIC LADDER.
BUT THEY DIDN'T
STAY THERE FOR LONG.
PAUL'S GREAT-GREAT GRANDFATHER
JOSEPH WOULD RISE UP,
WORKING FOR A BRICK MASON
BEFORE FOUNDING HIS OWN
CONSTRUCTION BUSINESS, AND
ASSURING HIS FAMILY'S SUCCESS.
RYAN: WOW.
GATES: WHAT'S IT
LIKE TO SEE THAT?
RYAN: I THINK IT'S
A BEAUTIFUL STORY.
I JUST LIKE THE FACT
THAT I'M A PART OF THE
WOVEN FABRIC OF THE COUNTRY.
I THINK THAT'S JUST
REALLY INTERESTING.
I THINK IT'S
GATES: YEAH, YEAH ME TOO.
RYAN: IT'S NEAT TO SEE WHAT
PEOPLE DO TO MAKE A BETTER
LIFE FOR THEMSELVES AND HOW
HARD IT WAS TO GET GOING IN
THIS COUNTY, TO
GET THINGS STARTED.
GATES: YEAH AND THEY
RISKED EVERYTHING.
RYAN: EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING.
GATES: AND THEY WERE
JUST GLAD TO BE HERE.
RYAN: THEY WALKED 50 MILES.
GATES: AND THEY
WALKED 50 MILES, YEAH.
RYAN: WHAT ARE THEY DOING,
HOW DID THEY DO THAT?
YEAH. IT'S NEAT.
GATES: IT'S INCREDIBLE.
RYAN: YEAH IT
REALLY IS, IT REALLY IS.
GATES: UNLIKE PAUL,
MARCO RUBIO KNOWS THE
IMMIGRANTS IN HIS FAMILY TREE.
THEY'RE HIS PARENTS, WHO
CAME TO THE UNITED STATES
FROM CUBA IN 1956.
BUT MARCO'S DEEPER ROOTS
WERE LARGELY A MYSTERY TO HIM.
AND AS WE BEGAN OUR RESEARCH,
WE SOON UNDERSTOOD WHY.
HIS FATHER, MARIO RUBIO REINA,
LOST BOTH OF HIS PARENTS BY
THE TIME HE WAS A TEENAGER,
AND ENDED UP LIVING ON THE
STREETS OF HAVANA.
A TRAUMA SO DEEP, IT
WAS RARELY DISCUSSED.
RUBIO: I KNOW VERY
LITTLE ABOUT HIS UPBRINGING.
I KNOW HIS MOTHER DIED
WHEN HE WAS VERY YOUNG OF
TUBERCULOSIS OR
SOME LUNG DISEASE.
AND THEN UH, HIS FATHER
AT SOME POINT REMARRIED,
AND UM, AND THEN,
WHEN HE WAS STILL
VERY YOUNG,
CERTAINLY BEFORE HE WAS 18,
HE MOVED OUT WITH ONE
OF HIS BROTHERS AND
LIVED SOMEWHERE ELSE.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS A GUY 14,
15 YEARS OF AGE ON HIS OWN.
GATES: AS IT TURNS OUT,
MARCO'S FATHER WASN'T THE
ONLY ONE IN HIS FAMILY TO
SUFFER SUCH LOSSES.
WE DISCOVERED THAT BOTH OF
MARIO'S PARENTS WERE ORPHANED
AT AN EARLY AGE, MEANING THAT
AT LEAST TWO GENERATIONS OF
MARCO'S ANCESTORS HAD TO FEND
FOR THEMSELVES AS CHILDREN.
RUBIO: YOU CAN BEGIN TO SEE
WHY SOME OF THESE STORIES WERE
NOT TOLD, ESPECIALLY THEY
DIDN'T HAVE, IF THEIR,
IF THESE KIDS WERE VERY
YOUNG WHEN THEIR PARENTS
DIED THEY JUST PROBABLY
DIDN'T KNOW AS MUCH ABOUT
THEIR PARENTS AND
COULDN'T PASS IT DOWN.
AND IT CERTAINLY
EXPLAINS A LOT ABOUT,
MY, MY FATHER
CERTAINLY WASN'T,
I DON'T THINK HE WAS ASHAMED
OF HIS FAMILY'S HISTORY,
HE JUST WASN'T A
PROMINENT FEATURE.
YOU WOULD THINK HE
KIND OF, YOU KNOW,
JUST APPEARED ON THE EARTH ONE
DAY AND THERE WAS NOTHING THAT
CAME BEFORE IT OTHER
THAN VERY VAGUE NOTIONS.
GATES: AND WHO WANTS TO
REVISIT ALL THAT PAIN?
RUBIO: YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
GATES: THAT'S SAD.
RUBIO: IT IS.
GATES: I WANTED TO RECOVER THE
STORIES THAT MARCO'S FAMILY
HAD LOST AMIDST
ALL THIS TRAGEDY.
ONE STOOD OUT AS
ESPECIALLY MEANINGFUL.
IT CONCERNS HIS
THIRD GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
A MAN NAMED JOSE
DE REINA Y TOSTA,
WHO WAS BORN AROUND
1760 IN SEVILLE, SPAIN.
JOSE'S BIRTHPLACE
WAS NOT UNEXPECTED,
AS MANY CUBANS HAVE
SPANISH ANCESTRY,
BUT HIS OCCUPATION TOOK
BOTH OF US BY SURPRISE.
RECORDS SHOW THAT HE
RECEIVED A LAW DEGREE
FROM THE UNIVERSITY OF GRANADA.
RUBIO: OH WOW.
HE'S A LAWYER.
GATES: 1786.
RUBIO: SO MY GREAT-
GREAT GRANDFATHER,
MY THIRD GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
WAS A LAWYER?
GATES: HE GOT A LAW DEGREE
200 YEARS BEFORE YOU DID.
RUBIO: WOW. WELL,
WE WAITED LONG ENOUGH.
THAT'S UNREAL.
THAT'S REALLY AMAZING.
GATES: YOU THOUGHT YOU
WERE THE FIRST LAWYER.
RUBIO: I THOUGHT I WAS.
GATES: WRONG.
RUBIO: THE FIRST IN TWO
CENTURIES. BUT UH, WOW.
GATES: AND GUESS WHAT?
HE WENT ON TO BECOME
A PUBLIC PROSECUTOR.
IN THE YEAR 1793 HE WAS
ADMITTED TO THE ATTORNEYS
PROFESSIONAL GUILD IN SEVILLE,
AND HE WENT ON TO BECOME A
PUBLIC PROSECUTOR.
RUBIO: SO, THERE YOU GO.
WELL, IT'S THE FIRST TIME I
READ ANYWHERE THAT ANYBODY IN
MY FAMILY HAD ANYTHING TO DO
WITH GOVERNMENT UP UNTIL ME.
GATES: JOSE NEVER REACHED THE
HEIGHTS THAT HIS DESCENDENT
MARCO HAS REACHED, BUT HIS
CAREER IN GOVERNMENT WAS
MARKED BY ONE
INCREDIBLE ACCOMPLISHMENT.
IN THE EARLY 1830S, JOSE
WAS SERVING IN MURCIA,
A PROVINCIAL CAPITAL,
WHEN A CHOLERA EPIDEMIC
STRUCK THE CITY.
AMIDST STAGGERING CASUALTIES,
JOSE FOUND HIMSELF THRUST INTO
THE SPOTLIGHT, COORDINATING
HEALTH AUTHORITIES,
THE POLICE, AND THE COURTS, AS
OTHER HIGH-RANKING OFFICIALS
DIED OR FLED.
RUBIO: SO HE WASN'T
JUST A GUY THAT WAS THERE,
PUNCHING THE CLOCK.
GATES: YOU'VE HAD TO
DEAL WITH HURRICANES.
RUBIO: YEAH?
GATES: CAN YOU RELATE
TO HIS HANDLING OF A
LARGE-SCALE CRISIS?
RUBIO: YEAH, EXCEPT THEY
DON'T HAVE THE RESOURCES
WE HAVE, YOU KNOW?
GATES: YEAH.
RUBIO: I MEAN JUST IMAGINING
HOW THIS THING WAS SPREADING,
PROBABLY HAD
PEOPLE CLOSE TO HIM.
THEY WERE LIVING THE
TRAGEDY ALONG WITH
HAVING TO ADMINISTER IT.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE YOU KNEW,
PEOPLE THAT WORKED FOR YOU ALL
OF A SUDDEN GOT SICK, SO YOUR
WORKFORCE WAS UNDER ATTACK.
IT MUST'VE BEEN AN EPIC CRISIS
AND VERY DIFFICULT TO HANDLE,
BUT HE COULD'VE
LEFT AND HE STAYED.
GATES: HOW'S
THAT MAKE YOU FEEL?
RUBIO: I GOT SOME
SHOES TO FILL, HUH?
GATES: JOSE
SURVIVED THE EPIDEMIC,
LIVING UNTIL HE WAS
ABOUT 70 YEARS OLD.
HIS SON, MARCO'S
GREAT-GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
ALSO TOOK UP GOVERNMENT WORK,
SERVING IN THE PAY CORPS OF
THE SPANISH ARMY.
SURVEYING THEIR LIVES,
MARCO WONDERED HOW THESE
ANCESTORS MAY HAVE
INFLUENCED HIM,
EVEN THOUGH THEIR
STORIES HAD BEEN LOST.
RUBIO: THOSE CAMPAIGNS
THAT I RAN MY DAD LOVED THEM,
I MEAN HE LOVED BEING INVOLVED
IN IT AND LOVED DOING IT.
I CAN'T IMAGINE HE
KNEW ANY OF THIS,
LIKE NO ONE'S EVER
TOLD US ANY OF THIS.
SO IT JUST KINDA
TELLS YOU THAT SOMEWHERE,
YOU KNOW, IN, IN THEIR BLOOD
BACK THEN IT WAS SOMEONE WHO
CARED ABOUT AND WAS INVOLVED
IN GOVERNMENT SERVICE AND,
AND THEN THERE WAS THESE
THINGS THAT MADE IT
IMPOSSIBLE FOR THREE
GENERATIONS TO DO IT,
AND THEN SUDDENLY YOU
PUT SOMEONE IN THE RIGHT
ENVIRONMENT AND THEY
WIND UP, YOU KNOW,
IN THE US SENATE.
THAT'S JUST UNBELIEVABLE.
GOD. WOW.
GATES: LIKE MARCO,
MY NEXT GUEST,
HAWAII'S TULSI GABBARD,
SEEMS TO HAVE INHERITED
A CALL TO SERVE.
INDEED, THE VERY REASON THAT
THE GABBARD FAMILY ENDED UP
IN THE PACIFIC AT ALL
LIES WITH THE MILITARY.
TULSI'S GREAT-GRANDFATHER, A
MAN NAMED BENJAMIN GABBARD,
CAME TO SAMOA AS A SAILOR
WITH THE U.S. NAVY.
AND WHILE ON LEAVE, HE
VISITED THE ISLAND OF APIA,
WHERE HE MET A LOCAL RESIDENT.
A WOMAN, NAMED CARRIE BARTLEY.
WE PICK UP THE COUPLE'S
STORY IN A 1920 EDITION OF
THE "SAMOA TIMES".
GABBARD: "A MAN-O'-WARSMAN
SPENT HIS WEEKEND AT APIA.
DURING HIS SHORT STAY HE WAS
MARRIED TO A SAMOAN BELLE,
THE BRIDE WAS
MISS CARRIE BARTLEY,
THE BRIDEGROOM,
MR. B.H. GABBARD,
WAS ATTENDED BY A
NUMBER OF HIS COMPANIONS
IN THE U.S. NAVY."
GATES: THAT'S YOUR
GREAT-GRANDPARENTS'
WEDDING ANNOUNCEMENT.
ISN'T THAT COOL?
GABBARD: THAT IS COOL.
"SAMOAN BELLE."
GATES: SAMOAN BELLE.
GABBARD: LITTLE DIFFERENT
THAN THE SOUTHERN BELLE.
GATES: INDEED.
THE NAVY WAS THE ONLY
REASON THAT HE WAS IN SAMOA,
WITHOUT IT YOU NEVER
WOULD HAVE BEEN BORN.
SO THANK GOD FOR THE NAVY.
GABBARD: YES.
GATES: TO TRACE THE ROOTS OF
TULSI'S GREAT-GRANDPARENTS,
WE FOUND OURSELVES
EXPLORING ARCHIVES
SCATTERED ACROSS THE GLOBE.
BENJAMIN'S ROOTS
STRETCH THROUGH KENTUCKY,
VIRGINIA AND
PENNSYLVANIA TO GERMANY!
CARRIE'S MOTHER
WAS A SAMOAN NATIVE,
WITH ANCESTORS WHO HAVE LIKELY
BEEN IN THE PACIFIC ISLANDS
FOR CENTURIES.
AND CARRIE'S FATHER, A
MAN NAMED CHARLES BARTLEY,
WAS BORN IN A PLACE
THAT TULSI HAD NEVER
ASSOCIATED WITH HER FAMILY.
WANT TO TAKE A WILD
GUESS WHERE WE FOUND HIM?
I'LL GIVE YOU A NICKEL.
GABBARD: I DON'T KNOW.
CALIFORNIA?
GATES: YOU LOSE.
GABBARD: I OWE YOU A NICKEL.
GATES: YOU OWE ME A NICKEL.
PLEASE TURN THE PAGE.
TULSI, ON THE RIGHT IS A BIRTH
REGISTER FROM THE YEAR 1858.
WOULD YOU PLEASE
READ THE TRANSCRIPTION?
SURPRISE.
GABBARD: "BIRTHS IN THE
DISTRICT OF AUCKLAND,
NEW ZEALAND.
GATES: TULSI, YOU HAVE
ROOTS IN NEW ZEALAND.
THIS IS WHERE YOUR
PEOPLE COME FROM.
DID YOU HAVE ANY IDEA?
GABBARD: NO. NO. WOW.
THIS IS REALLY COOL.
GATES: CHARLES
BARTLEY IS TULSI'S
GREAT-GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
AND HIS BIRTHPLACE POSED A
QUESTION: HOW DID SOMEONE BORN
IN NEW ZEALAND IN THE 1850S
END UP STARTING A FAMILY
IN SAMOA IN THE 1880S?
THE ANSWER LAY IN A
SAMOAN ENCYCLOPEDIA,
WHERE CHARLES' LIFE
SOUNDED LIKE THE PLOT
OF AN ADVENTURE NOVEL.
GABBARD: "MR. CHARLES BARTLEY,
STOREKEEPER AND TRADER,
OF SALANO, SAVAII, WAS
BORN IN AUCKLAND IN 1857,
BUT WAS EDUCATED IN APIA,
HAVING BEEN ONLY FIVE YEARS
OLD GONE WITH HIS
PARENTS TO SAMOA.
AT TEN YEARS OF AGE, HE
RAN AWAY TO SEA AND SPENT
12 YEARS IN A ROAMING LIFE."
GATES: WHAT A STORY!
ACCORDING TO
THIS ENCYCLOPEDIA,
YOUR FAMILY LEFT NEW ZEALAND
FOR SAMOA SOMETIME AROUND
1862, WHEN CHARLES
WAS FIVE YEARS OLD.
BUT CHARLES DIDN'T STAY
LONG IN HIS NEW HOME.
AS THIS TELLS US, AT THE
AGE OF TEN HE WENT TO SEA.
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
A TEN-YEAR-OLD ON A SHIP?
GABBARD: GOSH. NO.
GATES: HOW DO YOU THINK
STORIES LIKE THIS ARE LOST?
GABBARD: I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK THAT MY PARENTS
THEY'RE HUMBLE PEOPLE AND
I THINK SOMETIMES NOT
DOCUMENTING AND NOT TAKING
THE TIME TO FOCUS ON THIS
BECAUSE YOU'RE FOCUSING ON
WHAT'S RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU
STORIES LIKE THIS PROBABLY,
UM, FELL TO THE BACK.
GATES: WHAT'S YOUR DAD
GOING TO MAKE OF THIS STORY?
GABBARD: I THINK HE
WILL BE MIND-BLOWN.
GATES: WE CAN'T VERIFY THE
ENCYCLOPEDIA'S ACCOUNT OF
CHARLES' ROAMING YOUTH,
BUT WE DO KNOW THAT
HE DID, IN FACT, SETTLE
IN SAMOA AND THAT HE DID
INDEED BECOME A TRADER.
WE ALSO KNOW THAT AS AN ADULT,
CHARLES FACED A DAUNTING
CHALLENGE, ONE THAT WOULD HAVE
SPECIAL SIGNIFICANCE TO TULSI.
IN 1905, A SAMOAN
VOLCANO ERUPTED,
SENDING LAVA RUSHING STRAIGHT
TOWARDS CHARLES' DOOR.
GABBARD: "LAVA
SPREADS OVER ISLAND.
THE VOLCANO ON THE ISLAND
OF SAVAII IS STILL ACTIVE.
SOME PERSONS WILL NOT
LEAVE THEIR HOUSES UNTIL THE
DWELLINGS ARE ACTUALLY SET
ON FIRE BY THE BURNING LAVA.
THE LAVA HAS DESTROYED
ALL OF SALAGO, INCLUDING
THE HOME OF MR. BARTLEY,
A WELL-KNOWN RESIDENT."
GATES: CHARLES LOST HIS HOME.
GABBARD: GEEZ.
GATES: THIS ERUPTION WAS
HUGE INTERNATIONAL NEWS,
AND YOUR
GREAT-GREAT-GRANDFATHER
CHARLES WAS MENTIONED BY
NAME IN MANY ARTICLES,
IN MANY NEWSPAPERS.
IN FACT, A PHOTO OF HIS HOUSE
RIGHT BEFORE IT WAS DESTROYED
MADE IT INTO AN AUSTRALIAN
NEWSPAPER CALLED
"THE TOWN AND
COUNTRY JOURNAL."
THERE IT IS ON THE LEFT.
GABBARD: "MR. H. C.
BARTLEY'S HOUSE,
TAKEN AT 1 PM ON SATURDAY,
JANUARY 27, 1906.
LAVA CAN BE SEEN OVER
THE BUGGY IN THE DISTANCE,
SOME 60 YARDS AWAY.
THE HOUSE WAS BURNED AND STONE
COVERED HALFWAY UP THE WINDOWS
AT 11 O'CLOCK THE SAME NIGHT."
GATES: CAN YOU IMAGINE?
GABBARD: SADLY I CAN BECAUSE
WE ARE LITERALLY SEEING THIS
HAPPENING ON HAWAII ISLAND.
GATES: RIGHT NOW.
GABBARD: RIGHT NOW.
I WAS JUST THERE AND BOTH FLEW
OVER AND WALKED ON THE LAVA
THAT HAS BEEN SPOUTING.
GATES: WOW, THAT'S AMAZING.
GABBARD: AND IT'S JUST YEAH,
BEEN INCREDIBLE TO SEE HOW
COMPLETELY IT HAS
CHANGED EVERYTHING.
I MEAN HOUSES THAT I SAW,
FARMS THAT I SAW DURING THE
FIRST WEEK OF THE
ERUPTION NOW ARE,
IT'S LIKE THEY NEVER EXISTED.
GATES: THE VOLCANO ON CHARLES'
ISLAND CONTINUED TO ERUPT FOR
SIX YEARS, AND DESTROYED
MUCH OF WHAT HE OWNED.
BUT TULSI'S
ANCESTOR REFUSED TO FOLD .
GABBARD: "MR. BARTLEY IS THE
LARGEST LOSER BY THE PRESENT
VOLCANIC ERUPTION, HAVING
HAD HIS TWO STORES AND
CONTENTS BURNED, AND
HIS BOAT HAS ALSO GONE.
MR. BARTLEY, HOWEVER,
IS MADE OF STERN STUFF
AND IS NOT DISCOURAGED.
HE IS NOW PREPARING FOR
A FRESH START BEYOND THE
REACH OF THE PRESENT
VOLCANIC OUTBREAK."
GATES: STERN STUFF.
GABBARD: TRULY A TOUGH GUY.
GATES: YEAH. DOES THIS SOUND
LIKE ANYBODY IN YOUR FAMILY?
GABBARD: OH, YES.
GATES: PRETTY COOL.
GABBARD: YES.
THAT'S REALLY SPECIAL.
GATES: WE HAD ALREADY
TAKEN PAUL RYAN BACK TO HIS
GREAT-GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
JOSEPH HUTTER,
A GERMAN IMMIGRANT
WHO FOUNDED A
CONSTRUCTION BUSINESS
IN WISCONSIN.
NOW, WE WANTED TO GO FURTHER
ON THIS LINE, TO SEE WHERE
EXACTLY THE HUTTER
FAMILY ORIGINATED,
AND TRY TO LEARN WHY THEY
MADE THEIR JOURNEY TO AMERICA.
THESE ARE QUESTIONS THAT
HAVE LONG ANIMATED PAUL.
AS, GROWING UP, HIS
GERMAN ROOTS WERE NEVER AS
MUCH-DISCUSSED AS
HIS IRISH HERITAGE.
RYAN: I ALWAYS WONDERED
WHY THEY IMMIGRATED.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
BECAUSE I KNOW
THE FAMINE IRISH.
I KNOW THE IRISH STORY.
THAT'S A PRETTY
SIMPLE STORY, YOU KNOW.
GATES: YEAH, SURE.
RYAN: BUT I NEVER REALLY
KNEW THE BAVARIAN STORY,
BUT I DON'T KNOW IF
YOU KNOW THAT OR NOT.
YOU'RE GONNA GET THERE.
GATES: WAIT AND SEE.
RYAN: I HAVE NO CLUE.
I DON'T WHY.
GATES: TRACING PAUL'S FAMILY
IN GERMANY WOULD PROVE TO
BE A SUBSTANTIAL TASK.
WE KNEW THAT JOSEPH HUTTER
ARRIVED IN NEW YORK IN 1854,
BUT HIS ARRIVAL RECORD
DIDN'T NAME HIS HOMETOWN.
SO ALL WE HAD TO GO ON WAS A
FAMILY STORY THAT THE HUTTERS
ORIGINALLY CAME FROM BAVARIA.
FORTUNATELY, BAVARIAN CHURCHES
KEEP VERY GOOD RECORDS.
RYAN: JOHANNES HUTTER,
BORN JANUARY 6TH, 1812
IN HOCHABRUNN.
PARENTS: JOHANNES
HUTTER, WEAVER,
WEAVER IN HOCHABRUNN,
AND HIS WIFE MARGARETHA."
GATES: YOU'RE LOOKING AT
THE BAPTISMAL RECORD...
RYAN: HOW DO YOU
GUYS GET THIS STUFF?
GATES: FROM 1812 FOR YOUR
THIRD GREAT-GRANDFATHER,
YOUR GREAT-GREAT-
GREAT-GRANDFATHER'S
BAPTISMAL RECORD.
RYAN: HOW DID YOU GET THAT?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
GATES: AND JOHANNES OF
COURSE BECAME KNOWN AS JOHN.
RYAN: YEAH. MY GOSH.
GATES: WE NOW KNEW THAT
PAUL'S ANCESTORS CAME FROM
HOCHABRUNN, A VILLAGE ON
THE OUTSKIRTS OF THE TOWN OF
WALDMUCHEN IN EASTERN BAVARIA.
AND THIS ALLOWED US TO PROVIDE
SOME CONTEXT TO HIS FAMILY'S
DECISION TO EMIGRATE.
BY THE TIME THE
HUTTERS LEFT, IN 1854,
MOST OF HOCHABRUNN'S
POPULATION WERE TRADESPEOPLE
OR TENANT FARMERS,
EARNING A MEAGER LIVING,
OFTEN STRUGGLING
SIMPLY TO FEED THEMSELVES.
THEY LEFT LITTLE EVIDENCE
OF THEIR LIVES BEHIND,
BUT PAUL WAS THRILLED TO
SEE ANYTHING WE COULD FIND.
RYAN: "JOHANNES HUDERER.
BORN JANUARY 29,"
THAT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
GATES: OH, WOW.
RYAN: 1788 IN HOCHABRUNN.
"PARENTS: JOHANN", OH MY!
GATES: YEAH, JOHANN.
RYAN: "JOHANN ADAM HUDERER,
WEAVER IN HOCHABRUNN,
AND HIS WIFE BARBARA."
GATES: THIS IS ANOTHER
BAPTISMAL RECORD,
FOR YOUR FOURTH
GREAT-GRANDFATHER.
RYAN: FOURTH
GATES: YEAH, JOHANNES.
AND NOW...
RYAN: NOBODY IN MY ENTIRE
FAMILY KNOWS ANY OF THIS STUFF.
NOBODY KNOWS THIS STUFF.
GATES: WOW, THAT'S GREAT.
WELL YOU JUST MET ANOTHER
GENERATION OF YOUR FAMILY,
YOUR FIFTH GREAT-GRANDPARENTS,
HIS PARENTS JOHANN ADAM
HUDERER, ANOTHER WEAVER
AND HIS WIFE BARBARA,
BABL, JOHANN OR
ADAM AS HE WAS KNOWN,
WAS BORN APRIL 1,
READY FOR THIS?
1757 IN HOCHABRUNN.
RYAN: 1757.
GATES: 1757. THAT'S
18 YEARS BEFORE
THE BATTLES OF
CONCORD AND LEXINGTON.
RYAN: YEAH, RIGHT,
RIGHT. MY GOSH.
GATES: IT'S AMAZING.
WHAT'S IT LIKE TO
SEE THAT DOCUMENT?
RYAN: I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN'T, I NEVER, I DIDN'T
EXPECT YOU TO DO THIS.
WOW. THAT'S REALLY SOMETHING.
I DON'T REALLY
HAVE WORDS FOR THIS.
I'M AMAZED YOU
FOUND THIS STUFF.
GATES: YOU HAVE DEEP ROOTS IN
GERMANY AND WE DON'T KNOW FOR
SURE BUT WE THINK THEY CAME
FOR ECONOMIC OPPORTUNITY.
THAT'S THE ONLY
THING THAT MAKES SENSE.
RYAN: THAT'S MY GUESS,
I GUESS. I MEAN, YEAH...
GATES: LET ME
PUT IT THIS WAY..
RYAN: POOR FARMERS IN
BAVARIA AND THEY CAME FOR.
GATES: PEOPLE WITH A LOT
OF MONEY IN THE BANK
DON'T MIGRATE.
RYAN: YEAH. RIGHT,
RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT.
GATES: WE HAD ONE MORE
SURPRISE FOR PAUL:
A SECRET HIDDEN
WITHIN HIS OWN DNA.
WHEN WE ANALYZED
HIS ADMIXTURE,
WHICH REFLECTS HIS ANCESTRY
OVER ROUGHLY THE LAST
500 YEARS, WE DISCOVERED THAT
HIS HERITAGE WAS MORE VARIED
THAN THE PAPER
TRAIL HAD REVEALED.
COULD YOU READ YOUR
ADMIXTURE PERCENTAGES?
RYAN: OKAY.
61% IRISH/SCOTTISH/WELSH.
GATES: WHAT A SHOCK!
RYAN: WHAT A SHOCK!
61% IRISH.
15% SCANDINAVIAN,
9% EASTERN EUROPEAN,
3% ASHKENAZI JEWISH,
THAT'S REALLY COOL.
GATES: THAT IS A LOT.
RYAN: IS IT REALLY?
GATES: YEAH, THAT
MEANS SOMEWHERE,
THERE'S A JEWISH GUY THERE.
RYAN: THAT'S REALLY COOL.
YEAH, THERE'S A JEWISH
GUY IN THERE SOMEWHERE.
GATES: OR A WOMAN.
RYAN: YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
RIGHT! VERY COOL.
GATES: THREE PERCENTAGE POINTS
INDICATES THAT PAUL COULD HAVE
A THIRD GREAT-GRANDPARENT OF
FULL ASHKENAZI JEWISH DESCENT,
THOUGH IT IS ALSO POSSIBLE
THAT HE HAS MULTIPLE LINES
WITH MORE DISTANT
JEWISH ANCESTRY.
REGARDLESS, THE DNA
EVIDENCE IS UNEQUIVOCAL:
PAUL RYAN HAS JEWISH ROOTS.
A RESULT THAT HE WELCOMES,
AS A REFLECTION OF AMERICA'S
GREAT DIVERSITY.
RYAN: I THINK OF
THE MELTING POT.
I THINK OF THE FACT THAT YOU
CAN COME FROM ANY BACKGROUND
WHATSOEVER AND MAKE IT IN THIS
COUNTRY BECAUSE OF FREEDOM,
BECAUSE OF OUR SYSTEM,
BECAUSE OF PLURALISM.
GATES: IT'S WHO WE ARE.
IT'S PART OF OUR CULTURAL DNA.
RYAN: YEAH. I THINK
THAT'S FASCINATING.
GATES: YEAH, IT IS.
RYAN: IT IS.
GATES: WE'D ALREADY INTRODUCED
TULSI GABBARD TO HER
GREAT-GRANDFATHER BENJAMIN,
THE SAILOR WHO CAME TO SAMOA
WITH THE U.S. NAVY.
NOW, TURNING TO HER
MOTHER'S FAMILY TREE,
WE CAME UPON
ANOTHER MILITARY STORY,
FROM A VERY
DIFFERENT TIME AND PLACE.
TULSI'S THIRD
GREAT GRANDFATHER,
A MAN NAMED LEWIS PORTER,
GREW UP IN PENNSYLVANIA AS THE
UNITED STATES MOVED INEXORABLY
TOWARDS THE CIVIL WAR.
GATES: DID YOU HAVE ANY IDEA?
GABBARD: NO. NO.
I'VE, I'VE YOU KNOW, LOVED
READING ABOUT IT AND LEARNING
ABOUT IT AND YOU KNOW, WE'VE
GONE THROUGH GETTYSBURG
AND YOU KNOW, SEEN SOME OF
THE REENACTMENTS BUT I HAVE
NEVER IMAGINED THAT MY
ANCESTORS WERE THERE FOR THAT.
GATES: COULD YOU
PLEASE TURN THE PAGE?
NOW, YOU KNOW WHERE THE
NATIONAL ARCHIVES IS, RIGHT?
GABBARD: YES.
GATES: THIS IS A PAGE OF A
RECORD THAT WE FOUND IN THE
NATIONAL ARCHIVES.
WOULD YOU MIND READING
THE TRANSCRIBED SECTION?
GABBARD: "STATE OF OHIO,
TOWN OF WARREN.
I, LEWIS PORTER,
BORN IN PENNSYLVANIA,
AGE 40 YEARS, VOLUNTEERED THIS
31 DAY OF MARCH 1864 TO SERVE
AS A SOLDIER IN THE ARMY OF
THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA."
WOW!
GATES: YOUR GREAT-GREAT-
GREAT-GRANDFATHER
VOLUNTEERED TO FIGHT IN
THE UNION ARMY AGAINST THE
CONFEDERACY, HOW DOES
THAT MAKE YOU FEEL?
GABBARD: WOW. HONORED.
GATES: TULSI'S ANCESTOR
NOT ONLY VOLUNTEERED,
HE SERVED IN ONE OF THE
MOST SIGNIFICANT CAMPAIGNS
OF THE ENTIRE WAR.
IN THE SPRING OF 1864, JUST
WEEKS AFTER HE'D ENLISTED,
LEWIS PORTER'S REGIMENT SET
OFF UNDER GENERAL WILLIAM
TECUMSEH SHERMAN, ON HIS
FAMED ATLANTA CAMPAIGN.
WITH LITTLE TRAINING,
LEWIS SUDDENLY FOUND HIMSELF
MOVING SOUTH, STRAIGHT INTO THE
HEART OF THE CONFEDERACY.
NOW, YOU'VE SEEN COMBAT,
GABBARD: YEAH.
GATES: HOW DO YOU THINK
LEWIS MUST HAVE FELT?
GABBARD: OH, MY GOSH.
THIS IS A TOTALLY
DIFFERENT LEVEL I MEAN,
WHAT THEY, WHAT
THEY WENT THROUGH.
I ACTUALLY, AS PART OF MY
OFFICER CANDIDATE TRAINING,
IN ORDER TO EARN MY COMMISSION
AS A LIEUTENANT WE WENT AND
WALKED THROUGH THOSE
BATTLEFIELDS AND HEARD
ABOUT YOU KNOW, THE
TACTICS AND THE BATTLES
THAT WERE FOUGHT THERE.
GATES: AND IT NEVER OCCURRED
TO YOU THAT ONE OF YOUR
ANCESTORS COULD BE THERE.
GABBARD: GOSH, NO.
GATES: THAT'S AMAZING.
THAT IS AMAZING THAT
YOU'VE BEEN THERE.
GABBARD: IT WAS COOL JUST
TO BE THERE AND KIND OF
WALK THROUGH THOSE
FOOTSTEPS THAT THEY TOOK,
BUT UM, NO, I, THE THOUGHT
NEVER CROSSED MY MIND.
GATES: THE ATLANTA
CAMPAIGN WOULD PROVE
A SPECTACULAR SUCCESS.
BUT IT CAME AT A HEAVY COST.
THE UNION WAS OPPOSED BY
ONE OF THE LARGEST ARMIES
IN THE CONFEDERACY.
AND THE TWO FORCES SOON
FACED OFF AT A SMALL TOWN
IN NORTHERN GEORGIA
KNOWN AS RESACA.
FOR TWO DAYS, THE UNION
STRUGGLED TO DRIVE THE
CONFEDERATES FROM THE FIELD,
FIGHTING ON TERRAIN THAT WAS
ILL-SUITED FOR AN ATTACK.
LEWIS'S REGIMENT WAS
ON THE FRONT LINES.
WE FOUND A NEWSPAPER ARTICLE,
WRITTEN JUST WEEKS
AFTER THE BATTLE,
THAT DESCRIBES
WHAT THEY ENDURED.
GABBARD: "PORTIONS
OF PALMER'S CORPS,
IN ATTEMPTING TO
CHARGE THE REBELS IN FRONT,
WERE COMPELLED TO WADE
A CREEK WAIST DEEP, WHICH
RAN AT THE FOOT OF THE BLUFF;
AND THEN ACROSS A
VALLEY FILLED WITH DITCHES,
FULLY EXPOSED TO A FIRE
FROM THE REBEL WORKS.
NEVER DID MEN GO TO
WORK MORE GALLANTLY,
OR CONTEST MORE NOBLY; BUT
THEY COULD NOT ACCOMPLISH
IMPOSSIBILITIES, AND,
AFTER SEVERE LOSS,
WERE OBLIGED TO WITHDRAW."
GATES: COULD YOU IMAGINE?
GABBARD: IT'S TOUGH.
GATES: NOW, WE DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED TO LEWIS
IN THAT BATTLE, BUT HIS
REGIMENT WAS ASSAULTING THE
VERY SAME CENTER STRETCH
OF THE CONFEDERATE LINE
DESCRIBED IN THAT ARTICLE.
HE AND HIS COMRADES LIKELY
DESCENDED A STEEP RIDGE,
AND THEN CROSSED A CREEK
AND SCALED AN ALMOST VERTICAL
SLOPE WHERE THE CONFEDERATES
HAD DUG EARTHWORKS,
ALL THE WHILE EXPOSED
TO DIRECT ENEMY
ARTILLERY AND RIFLE FIRE.
GABBARD: JEEZ.
GATES: SO HE WAS OUT THERE.
I MEAN HE WAS EXPOSED.
HE WAS ON THE LINE.
DO YOU FEEL A SENSE
OF PRIDE? FOR YOUR...
GABBARD: I DO, I
REALLY DO. JUST...
GATES: KNOWING THAT THIS GUY
EXISTS ON YOUR FAMILY TREE?
GABBARD: ABSOLUTELY.
YOU KNOW?
IT SAYS A LOT ABOUT THIS
ETHIC OF SERVICE...
GATES: INDEED.
GABBARD: GOING BACK MUCH
FARTHER THAN I KNEW.
GATES: LEWIS PORTER
SURVIVED RESACA,
BUT SOON FACED AN
EVEN GREATER ORDEAL.
JUST DAYS AFTER THE
BATTLE, HE TOOK ILL,
AND WAS SENT TO A
FIELD HOSPITAL.
HE NEVER FULLY RECOVERED.
OVER THE NEXT SIX MONTHS,
LOUIS WAS TREATED IN FOUR
DIFFERENT HOSPITALS, SUFFERING
FROM STOMACH AILMENTS THAT
WOULD PERSIST FOR
DECADES FOLLOWING THE WAR.
ONE OF HIS DOCTOR'S DESCRIBED
HIS CONDITION IN SOME DETAIL,
AS PART OF LEWIS'S APPLICATION
FOR AN INVALID PENSION,
FILED IN 1882.
GABBARD: "I HAVE CAREFULLY
EXAMINED LEWIS PORTER,
LATE A PRIVATE, CO. A.,
105TH REG'T, OHIO INFANTRY
WHO IS AN APPLICANT
FOR AN INVALID PENSION,
THE SAID LEWIS PORTER IS
ONE-FOURTH INCAPACITATED.
THE DISABILITY IS
PROBABLY PERMANENT.
LEWIS PORTER STATES THAT
HE SUFFERS AND THAT HE IS
LABORING UNDER THE
DISEASE AT THIS TIME."
THIS IS 1882.
GATES: HE WAS DISCHARGED
FROM THE ARMY ON
JULY 22ND, 1865, I MEAN
THE POOR GUY IS STILL.
GABBARD: SUFFERING STILL.
I MEAN THIS UNFORTUNATELY
UM, I MEAN THIS REMINDS ME
OF WHAT I HEAR FROM
VIETNAM VETERANS
WHO CALL AND ASK FOR
HELP AND WHO SIMILARLY
DECADES, DECADES
AFTER COMING HOME
ARE STILL SUFFERING.
GATES: YEAH.
GABBARD: YOU CAN TALK
ABOUT THE DOLLARS AND CENTS,
BUT IT'S NOT TAKING INTO
ACCOUNT THE HUMAN COST AND
WHAT OUR COUNTRY PROMISES
TO THOSE WHO GO AND SERVE.
GATES: WE PROMISE THEM
EVERYTHING AND THEN
TREAT THEM AS IF THEY'RE AN
EMBARRASSMENT TO THE COUNTRY.
GABBARD: SADLY.
GATES: LEWIS PORTER SUFFERED
A GREAT DEAL FOR HIS COUNTRY,
BUT HIS STORY HAS A
SURPRISINGLY HAPPY ENDING.
RECORDS SHOW THAT LEWIS
LIVED TO BE 86 YEARS OLD,
NOT ONLY THAT, HE MANAGED
TO HAVE A FULL LIFE
DESPITE HIS ILLNESS,
MARRYING THREE TIMES,
AND FATHERING AT
LEAST 12 CHILDREN.
GATES: HE MIGHT HAVE BEEN
SICK BUT HE WASN'T DEAD.
GABBARD: THAT'S RIGHT.
GATES: WHAT'S IT BEEN LIKE
FOR YOU TO LEARN THIS STORY?
GABBARD: IT'S INCREDIBLE AND
EXCITING TO HEAR AND IN MY OWN
VERY SMALL WAY BE ABLE TO
RELATE IN SOME FASHION TO THE
CHOICES THAT HE MADE
UM, TO VOLUNTEER AND UM,
GOSH, WHAT HE WENT THROUGH.
GATES: DID IT EVER OCCUR TO
YOU WHEN YOU'RE FIGHTING TO
GET YOUR NAME ADDED TO THE
DEPLOYMENT LIST THAT BASICALLY
YOU'RE CHANNELING YOUR
THIRD GREAT-GRANDFATHER.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE
CARRYING OUT A TRADITION.
GABBARD: NOW I KNOW
WHERE I GET IT FROM.
GATES: YEAH. THAT'S
ASTONISHING, ISN'T IT?
GABBARD: THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
YEAH.
GATES: WE HAD ALREADY TRACED
MARCO RUBIO'S FATHER'S FAMILY
FROM THE STREETS OF HAVANA
TO THE COURTYARDS OF SEVILLE.
NOW, TURNING TO
HIS MOTHER'S ROOTS,
WE EXPECTED TO MAKE
A SIMILAR JOURNEY,
BUT OUR SEARCH
LED US ELSEWHERE.
WE STARTED WITH
MARCO'S GRANDFATHER,
PEDRO GARCIA, A MAN WHOSE
LIFE WAS MARKED BY HARDSHIP.
RUBIO: MY GRANDFATHER HAD
AN UP OR DOWN EXISTENCE.
YOU KNOW, HE AT ONE POINT HAD
A PRETTY GOOD JOB WORKING IN
A, FOR THE RAILROAD COMPANY
OR WHATEVER IT WAS AND
THEN HE LOST THAT JOB,
AND THEN HE STRUGGLED.
HE HAD BEEN UH, HANDICAPPED
AS A BOY WITH POLIO.
AND THERE WERE TIMES WHERE HE
REALLY STRUGGLED TO PROVIDE
FOR THEM BECAUSE
PHYSICALLY HE COULDN'T,
YOU KNOW, DO SOME OF THE WORK
THAT OTHER PEOPLE COULD DO.
GATES: PEDRO IMMIGRATED TO
AMERICA FROM CUBA IN THE 1950S.
MARCO KNEW HIM, AND
REMEMBERS HIM FONDLY AS
A MAN WHO LOVED HISTORY
AND LOVED STORY-TELLING.
BUT PEDRO RARELY SPOKE
ABOUT HIS CHILDHOOD,
AND MARCO KNOWS NEXT TO
NOTHING ABOUT HIS ROOTS.
RUBIO: I JUST KNOW HE WAS
ONE OF A LOT OF KIDS AND,
AND YOU KNOW, THE STORY
ALWAYS WAS HIS PARENTS,
I'M NOT SURE
WERE EVEN MARRIED.
GATES: MARCO, THEY
HAD 17 CHILDREN.
RUBIO: ALL FROM HER?
GATES: ALL FROM HER.
RUBIO: THAT'S SOMETHING ELSE.
GATES: THAT'S HARD WORK.
RUBIO: YEAH.
GATES: DO YOU HAVE ANY
IDEA WHERE THIS PART OF
YOUR FAMILY CAME FROM?
RUBIO: I DON'T.
WE ARE NOW AT THE LIMITS OF
MY KNOWLEDGE OF MY FAMILY'S
ANCESTRY, RIGHT HERE.
GATES: TO PUSH BEYOND THE
LIMITS OF MARCO'S KNOWLEDGE
REQUIRED SOME LUCK.
WE WERE ABLE TO LEARN VERY
LITTLE ABOUT PEDRO'S FATHER
CARLOS, AND WE COULD ONLY
TRACE HIS MOTHER RAMONA BACK
ONE GENERATION, TO THE 1850S.
BUT TURNING TO PEDRO'S WIFE,
A WOMAN NAMED DOMINGA
RODRÍGUEZ Y CHIROLDE,
WE WERE ABLE TO GO MUCH
FURTHER BACK IN TIME.
MANY OF HER ANCESTORS
LIVED IN PINAR DEL RÍO,
A LARGELY RURAL
PROVINCE IN WESTERN CUBA,
WHERE WE FOUND A SERIES OF
BAPTISM AND MARRIAGE RECORDS
TAKING HER ROOTS
BACK ALMOST 300 YEARS.
MEANING MARCO RUBIO'S FAMILY
HAS LIVED IN CUBA FOR MUCH
LONGER THAN HE EVER DREAMED.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT THE NAME OF
YOUR FIFTH GREAT-GRANDFATHER.
RUBIO: MANUEL
RICARDO DEL ALDANA?
GATES: HAVE YOU
EVER HEARD OF HIM?
RUBIO: NO.
GATES: HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF THAT SURNAME, ALDANA?
RUBIO: I'VE HEARD IT,
BUT I CAN'T CONNECT IT
TO ANYBODY OR ANYTHING.
GATES: YOUR FIFTH GREAT-
GRANDFATHER WOULD'VE
BEEN BORN AROUND 1730.
RUBIO: 1730.
GATES: SENATOR, THERE ARE
A LOT OF AMERICANS WHOSE
ANCESTRY HAILS FROM
NORTHERN EUROPE WHO
CANNOT GO BACK THIS FAR.
RUBIO: GET THIS FAR? YEAH.
GATES: IN THEIR FAMILY TREE.
RUBIO: YEAH. THAT'S
AMAZING, IT REALLY IS.
NO ONE CAN SAY I'M NOT CUBAN.
GATES: NOBODY.
RUBIO: YEAH.
GATES: MARCO WAS SURPRISED TO
SEE THAT HIS MATERNAL ROOTS
RAN SO DEEPLY IN CUBA,
HE'D EXPECTED THEM TO
TRACE IN THE NEAR
PAST BACK TO SPAIN,
AS WE'D SEEN ON
HIS FATHER'S SIDE.
BUT HE WAS EVEN MORE SURPRISED
BY WHAT RECORDS REVEALED ABOUT
HIS THIRD GREAT-GRANDFATHER, A
MAN NAMED JUAN JOSÉ CHIROLES.
HE WAS A LANDOWNER.
HE OWNED A TOBACCO FARM.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
RUBIO: I DID NOT.
I HAD NO CLUE.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME EVER THAT
SOMEONE SAYS THAT ANYBODY IN
MY LINEAGE OWNED ANYTHING
IN CUBA BEYOND THE
CLOTHES ON THEIR BACK.
GATES: AS IT TURNS OUT, JUAN
OWNED ROUGHLY 30 ACRES OF LAND
ON WHICH HE GREW
TOBACCO, CORN AND RICE,
BUT THAT WASN'T ALL HE OWNED.
WE FOUND THE BAPTISMAL RECORD
FOR A CHILD BORN TO HIS SLAVE.
RUBIO: "I, THE PINAR
DEL RÍO PARISH PRIEST,
SOLEMNLY BAPTIZED ISABEL, BORN
ON THE 19TH OF LAST MONTH,
DAUGHTER OF THE "MOREAN
CRIOLLA" ANGELA AND AN
UNKNOWN FATHER, BOTH SLAVES
OF JUAN JOSÉ CHIROLDE,
WHO LIVES IN THIS PARISH."
WOW.
THAT'S WHAT I FEARED WHEN WE
WERE GOING INTO THIS WHOLE
EXPERIENCE ABOUT THE
LAND AND SO FORTH.
THAT WAS GONNA BE MY
FOLLOW-UP QUESTION,
BUT I DIDN'T WANT TO
KNOW THE ANSWER, SO.
GATES: DID YOU EVER IMAGINE
THAT YOU HAD A SLAVE OWNER
IN YOUR FAMILY TREE?
RUBIO: NO, I DIDN'T.
I MEAN I DIDN'T THINK
THEY OWNED ANY LAND,
SO I DIDN'T THINK
THEY COULD OWN PEOPLE.
GATES: WHAT ARE YOU FEELING?
RUBIO: IT'S JUST HARD TO
KIND OF PROCESS IT ALL.
I MEAN IF YOU BAPTIZED THEM
IT'S BECAUSE YOU BELIEVED THEY
HAD A SOUL AND WERE
CREATED IN GOD'S IMAGE.
HOW THEN COULD
YOU OWN THEM AS A,
AS A PIECE OF
CATTLE OR YOU KNOW AND,
AND, AND AS A, AS, I
JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT.
GATES: DOES THIS CHANGE THE
WAY THAT YOU THINK OF THIS
PART OF YOUR FAMILY'S HISTORY?
RUBIO: YEAH.
I MEAN OBVIOUSLY IT'S JUST
NOT SOMETHING I EVER THOUGHT,
YOU KNOW, I
NEVER THOUGHT OF IT.
I JUST DIDN'T
THINK IT WAS THERE.
YOU SORT OF SEE LIKE ONE
GENERATION OWNS LAND AND
UM, SADLY OWNS HUMAN
BEINGS AND ALL THAT,
AND, AND WITHIN
TWO GENERATIONS,
I MEAN, THEY'RE BARELY
FEEDING THEIR KIDS,
AND THEY'RE STRUGGLING TO
PROVIDE FOR THEIR FAMILIES.
I MEAN IT JUST TELLS YOU
HOW QUICKLY PEOPLE'S
FORTUNES CHANGE, RIGHT?
GATES: REVERSAL OF FORTUNE.
RUBIO: WOW.
GATES: THE PAPER TRAIL HAD NOW
RUN OUT FOR EACH OF MY GUESTS.
IT WAS TIME TO SEE WHAT
DNA COULD REVEAL ABOUT
THEIR DEEPER ROOTS.
WE'D ALREADY SHOWN PAUL RYAN
THAT HIS ADMIXTURE REVEALED
HIDDEN JEWISH ANCESTRY.
FOR TULSI GABBARD, THE SAME
TEST REFLECTED THE ENORMOUS
DIVERSITY WE'D SEEN
IN HER GENEALOGY,
TYING HER TO ETHNIC
GROUPS ACROSS THE GLOBE,
FROM NORTHERN EUROPE,
TO SOUTHEAST ASIA!
GABBARD: GOSH.
THIS JUST SHOWS HOW
CONNECTED WE ALL ARE.
GATES: INDEED.
GABBARD: THIS IS
FURTHER PROOF AND EVIDENCE.
WHEN WE LOOK AT OUR LIVES AND
THOSE WHO'VE COME BEFORE US
WE'RE ALL CONNECTED.
GATES: WE'RE ALL CONNECTED.
TURNING TO MARCO RUBIO, WE HAD
ONE FINAL REVELATION TO SHARE.
WHEN WE ANALYZED HIS
MITOCHONDRIAL DNA,
A GENETIC FINGERPRINT PASSED
DOWN UNCHANGED FROM MOTHER TO
CHILD FOR THOUSANDS OF YEARS,
WE FOUND THAT HIS DIRECT
MATERNAL LINE WAS
NATIVE AMERICAN.
ONE OF YOUR GREAT-GREAT-
GREAT-GRANDMOTHERS
WAS A PURE NATIVE AMERICAN.
RUBIO: YEAH, WOW,
LOOK AT THAT.
GATES: SCHOLARS BELIEVE THAT
THE NATIVE AMERICAN POPULATION
IN PINAR DEL RÍO MIGRATED
FROM THE YUCATÁN PENINSULA
ABOUT 4000 BC.
RUBIO: RIGHT.
GATES: SO, TALK
ABOUT, YOU KNOW,
ANCESTRAL ROOTS IN CUBA, YOUR
FAMILY ON YOUR NATIVE AMERICAN
LINE'S BEEN THERE
FOR A LONG, LONG TIME.
RUBIO: RIGHT. I'VE BEEN TO
THOSE RUINS IN THE YUCATÁN.
GATES: OH YEAH?
RUBIO: AT CHICHEN ITZA,
AND WHO KNEW I WAS
GOING BACK HOME?
GATES: MARCO'S DNA UNDERSCORES
A LARGER POINT: ALMOST EVERY
AMERICAN DESCENDS FROM
SOMEONE WHO WASN'T BORN
IN OUR COUNTRY, BUT HAS
EMBRACED, AND ENRICHED
IT JUST THE SAME.
WE'D SEEN THIS OVER AND OVER
IN MY GUESTS' FAMILY TREES,
AND ITS RELEVANCE WASN'T
LOST ON ANY OF THEM,
LEAST OF ALL ON MARCO RUBIO.
RUBIO: THIS REALLY BRINGS
IT TO LIGHT ABOUT AMERICA.
IN AMERICA WE DON'T
HAVE A COMMON ETHNICITY,
A COMMON LANGUAGE.
I MEAN THERE'S, THERE ARE
COUNTRIES IN THIS WORLD THAT
DOING THE DNA OF THE
POPULATION WOULD NOT BE
VERY COMPLICATED, EVERYONE AT
SOME POINT IS PRETTY SIMILAR.
GATES: LIKE ICELAND.
RUBIO: LIKE, YEAH, RIGHT.
SO, I, AND OTHER PLACES.
AND, BUT IN AMERICA WE'RE,
IT'S NOT JUST A GENETIC MIX.
WE COME FROM DIFFERENT
CONTINENTS AND DIFFERENT
PARTS OF THE WORLD.
IF YOU GO FAR ENOUGH,
WE COME FROM EVERYWHERE.
BUT I'VE ALWAYS SAID THAT THE
ONE THING WE HAVE IN COMMON
IN ALL OF OUR DNA AS
AMERICANS IS WE ALL
DESCEND FROM GO-GETTERS.
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF US
DESCENDS FROM SOMEONE
WHO OVERCAME INCREDIBLE
ADVERSITY, WHETHER IT WAS
UH, THE JOURNEY THAT
BROUGHT THEM INTO,
INTO SLAVERY AND THEN SURVIVED
IT IN BRUTAL CONDITIONS FOR
HUNDREDS OF YEARS, WHETHER
IT'S SOMEONE WHO CAME LAST
WEEK FROM ANOTHER COUNTRY
IN SEARCH OF A BETTER LIFE,
OR SOMEONE WHO CAME
200 YEARS AGO IN
SEARCH OF A BETTER LIFE.
OUR COMMON DNA IN AMERICA IS
WE ALMOST ALL DESCEND FROM A
GO-GETTER, SOMEONE WHO REFUSED
TO ACCEPT THE LIMITS PUT UPON
THEM IN THE OLD WORLD, AND
SO THEY REACHED FOR THIS ONE
PLACE WHERE THEY WERE GONNA
BE JUDGED BY WHO THEY WERE,
NOT WHERE THEY CAME FROM.
GATES: THAT'S THE END
OF OUR JOURNEY WITH
MARCO, TULSI, AND PAUL.
JOIN ME NEXT TIME
WHEN WE UNLOCK THE
SECRETS OF THE PAST
FOR NEW GUESTS ON
ANOTHER EPISODE OF
"FINDING YOUR ROOTS".
TO ORDER THIS PROGRAM ON DVD,
VISIT SHOP PBS OR CALL
1-800-PLAY-PBS.
THIS PROGRAM IS ALSO AVAILABLE
ON AMAZON PRIME VIDEO.
NARRATOR: CORPORATE FUNDING
FOR "FINDING YOUR ROOTS"
WAS PROVIDED BY:
WHEN WE LEARN
ERE WE COME FROM,
WE LEARN A DEEPER
STORY ABOUT OURSELVES.
AT ANCESTRY, THERE
ARE DIFFERENT PATHS
TO DISCOVERING YOUR STORY.
FROM BUILDING
YOUR FAMILY TREE,
TO LEARNING YOUR
FULL ETHNICITY
AND REVEALING ANCESTORS
YOU NEVER KNEW YOU HAD.
ANCESTRY HELPS YOU CONNECT
TO YOUR UNIQUE STORY.
MAN: WE ALL COME FROM SUCH
DIFFERENT BACKGROUNDS
THAT YOU NEVER KNOW.
NARRATOR: LEARN MORE
AT ANCESTRY.COM.
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER WE'VE
ALWAYS BEEN CONNECTED.
AT AT&T WE'RE CONTINUING TO
CREATE TECHNOLOGY THAT WILL
HELP PEOPLE STAY CONNECTED
NOW AND INTO THE FUTURE.
IN THE 1950S JAUNDICE WAS A
LEADING CAUSE OF INFANT DEATH.
UNTIL A NURSE FOUND
THAT SUNLIGHT COULD CURE
THE CONDITION.
MAJOR FUNDING WAS PROVIDED BY:
THE FORD FOUNDATION,
WORKING WITH VISIONARIES ON THE
FRONT LINES OF
SOCIAL CHANGE WORLDWIDE.
BY CANDACE KING WEIR,
THE LLOYD CARNEY FOUNDATION,
THE ROBERT WOOD
JOHNSON FOUNDATION,
BY THE CORPORATION
FOR PUBLIC BROADCASTING
AND BY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO THIS PBS STATION
FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU,
THANK YOU.
♪ ♪
BE MORE PBS