RESOURCES.
>> Dana: THANKS.
A HORRIFYING MOMENT CAUGHT ON
CAMERA.
A UTAH WOMAN WAS DRIVING WITH
THREE KIDS WHEN SHE SAW A MAN IN
THE ROAD.
SHE HONKED BUT HE TURNED AND
HEADED TOWARDS HER.
SHE PARKED AND TRIED TO LOCKED
THE DOORS.
SHE DIDN'T DO SO IN TIME.
THE GOOD NEWS IS, A GOOD
SAMARITAN STOPPED THE MAN.
FRITZ PARKED HIS CAR IN FRONT OF
CARJACKER.OCKED THE PATH OF
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
I'M DANA.
HERE'S SHEP.
>> Shepard: DID YOU HEAR THIS?
THE CHINESE ARE USING OUR OWN
AMERICAN SATELLITES AGAINST US.
IT'S A STUNNING NEW REPORT ON
SATELLITES BUILT BY AMERICANS
THAT BEIJINGb( USING TO■■ HELP
ITS POLICE AND SOLDIERS.
PLUS, LORI LOUGHLIN'S AREAS
ASKING THE GOVERNMENT TO TURN
OVER THE EVIDENCE.
HER AND HER HUSBAND FACING THE
POSSIBILITY OF DECADES BEHIND
BARS IF CONVICTED.
AND NOW BOB SAGET WEIGHING
IN.
REPORTING BEGINS NOW.
AND OUR REPORTING BEGINS WITH
BREAKING NEWS THIS HOUR.
HILLARY CLINTON SPEAKING OUT
ABOUT THE SPECIAL COUNSEL ROBERT
MUELLER'S FINAL REPORT ON THE
RUSSIA INVESTIGATION.
THE FORMER SECRETARY OF STATE
AND ONE-TIME CANDIDATE CALLING
FOR THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT TO
RELEASE THE UNREDACTED VERSION
AND SAVE -- AND SAYING THE
MUELLER REPORT IS JUST THE
BEGINNING.
>> I'M REALLY OF THE MIND THAT
THE MUELLER REPORT IS PART OF
THE BEGINNING.
IT'S NOT THE END.
MAYBE AS CHURCHILL SAID, IT'S
THE END OF THE BEGINNING.
THERE'S STILL SO MUCH MORE THAT
WE SHOULD KNOW AND THAT WE
SHOULD ACT UPON.
OBVIOUSLY THAT'S WHAT THE
CONGRESS IS TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT, WHAT TO DO RIGHT NOW.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
SON-IN-LAW AND SENIOR ADVISER
CLAIMED THE RUSSIAN
INVESTIGATION HAS BEEN MORE
DAMAGING TO THE UNITED STATES
THAN PUTIN'S MEDDLING IN THE
2016 ELECTION.
JARED KUSHNER SPEAKING PUBLICLY
FOR THE FIRST TIME SINCE THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL ROBERT MUELLER'S
REDACTED FINAL REPORT CAME OUT
LAST WEEK.
JARED KUSHNER SAID HE THOUGHT
THE WHOLE THING WAS KIND OF
NONSENSE.
THAT'S A QUOTE.
HERE'S WHAT HE SAID TODAY DURING
THE TIME 100 SUMMIT.
>> YOU LOOK AT WHAT RUS DID,
ACEBOODS ANDTO 7p7p7p7p7p■p■p■p
NVESTIGATIONS
AND ALL OF THE SPECULATION THAT
HAS HAPPENED THE LAST TWO YEARS
HAS HAD A MUCH HARSHER IMPACT
THAN A COUPLE OF FACEBOOK ADS.
>> Shepard: JARED KUSHNER'S
DIMINISHMENT OF RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE IS DECEPTIVE.
FROM THE MUELLER REPORT WE NOW
KNOW, RUSSIANS MADE CONTACT WITH
MULTIPLE MEMBERS OF THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN, INCLUDING JARED
KUSHNER AND ATTEMPTING TO
PROMOTE RUSSIAN OBJECTIVES.
THEY RECEIVED CAMPAIGN POLLING
DATA FROM THE TRUMP TEAM AND
DISCUSSED BUSINESS DEALS AND
POLICY GOALS AND GETTING DIRT ON
HILLARY CLINTON WITH THE NOW
PRESIDENT'S SON AND OTHERS.
THEY CONDUCTED CYBER ESPIONAGE,
STEALING E-MAILS AND
DISTRIBUTING THEM TO HELP
CANDIDATE TRUMP AND HURT TRUMP'S
OPPONENT.
THEY SENT RUSSIAN OPERATIVES IN
AMERICA IN PERSON TO LEARN THE
LANDSCAPE AND SOW DIVISION IN
AMERICA.
THAT I BROKE INTO STATE AND
LOCAL ELECTION COMPUTERS AND
INVADED OUR NATION IN THE CYBER
AND PHYSICAL WORLDS.
THE UNITED STATES INDICTED 26
RUSSIAN NATIONALS AND THREE
RUSSIAN COMPANIES AND THE
MUELLER REPORT MAKE CRYSTAL
CLEAR AND ALL U.S. INTELLIGENCE
AGENCIES CONCUR THE RUSSIANS ARE
STILL TRYING TO THING OUR
NATION, INTERFERE IN OR AFFAIRS
AND INFLUENCE OUR ELECTIONS.
SPECIAL COUNSEL PROSECUTORS
INTERVIEWED JARED KUSHNER FOR
HIS CONTACTS WITH THE RUSSIANS
INCLUDING THE INFAMOUS TRUMP
TOWER MEETING WITH DONALD TRUMP
JR. AND THE PRESIDENT'S CAMPAIGN
CHAIRMAN, PAUL MANAFORT.
MUELLER REPORT WHILE THERE'S
EVIDENCE OF COMMUNICATIONS WITH
THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND MOSCOW,
THERE WAS NO COORDINATION.
ON THE MATTER OF RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE, THE FACEBOOK ADS
JARED KUSHNER REFERENCES WERE
BUT A SLIVER OFRUSSIA'S ATTACK
@A.
JOHN ROBH MORE.
>> GOOD AFTERNOON TO A=A=A=A=
IT WAS INTERESTING TO HEAA=A=A==
SIA=LLERREAA=A=A=A=A=A=A=A=A=A==
A=A=A=A=A=A=A=A=A=A=A=A=A=A=A=A
2016 MEETING AT TRUMP TOWERS.
IN THE REPORT, MUELLER SUGGESTED
THAT HE WAS CONSIDERING WHETHER
OR NOT THAT MEETING MIGHT HAVE
CONSTRUED AN ILLEGAL CAMPAIGN
CONTRIBUTION FROM A FOREIGN
SOURCE.
BUT ULTIMATELY MUELLER'S
INVESTIGATORS COULD NOT FIGURE
OUT WHETHER THERE WAS ANYTHING S
OPERATIVE WAS
HERE'S WHAT KUSHNER SAID OR WHAT
ELSE HE SAID ABOUT THE MUELLER
REPORT.
WITH THE WHOLE NOTION OF THE
RUSSIA COLLUSION NARRATIVE CAME
UP, I WAS THE FIRST PERSON TO
SAY HAPPY TO PARTICIPATE WITH
ANY INVESTIGATIONS.
AT THIS POINT, I'VE DOWN THREE
HOURS INTERVIEWS, NINE HOURS OF
SPECIAL COUNSEL.
LOOK AT MANY STATEMENT FROM
JULY, I PUT OUT ABOUT A 12-PAGE
STATEMENT EXPLAINING ALL OF
THESE THINGS.
EVERYTHING I HAVE SAID IS TRUE
AND VERY, VERY THOROUGHLY
INVESTIGATED.
THE ONE THING THE MUELLER REPORT
WAS CONCLUSIVE ON IS THERE WAS
ABSOLUTELY NO COORDINATION ORA==
GN.
NOA SAY THATA= THEA=A=A=A=A=A=AO
ABOUT THE SUBPOENA THATA=A=A=ST
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE, GERALDAAAA
21 FROA=R WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL, DON McGAHN.
IN A STATEMENT, GERALD NADLER
SAYING --
>> McGAHN MET WITH INVESTIGATORS
MORE THAN 30 HOURS.
IT'S UNCLEAR WHAT MORE CONGRESS
COULD LEARN IN A HEARING THAN
MUELLER DID IN 30 HOURS OF
QUESTIONING.
IT'S UNCLEAR WHETHER THE WHITE
HOUSE WILL ALLOW McGAHN TO
TESTIFY OR EXERT EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE.
MIGHT BE DIFFICULT TO MAKE THAT
CLAIM IN A COURT OF LAW.
THEY DID NOT CLAIM ANY PRIVILEGE
OVER ANYTHING IN THE MUELLER
REPORT THAT HAD McGAHN'S NAME ON
IT.
THEY ALSO DID NOT ASSERT
ATTORNEY CLIENT PRIVILEGE AND
NOT ALLOW HIM TO DO AN INTERVIEW
WITH ROBERT MUELLER.
PUTTING THE GENIE OF EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE OR ATTORNEY CLIENT
PRIVILEGE IN THE BOTTLE MAY BE
DIFFICULT.
THE FORMER CHAIRMAN OF THE HOUSE
COMMITTEE DARRELL ISSA SAID THAT
HE BELIEVES McGAHN WILL TESTIFY
BUT WITH A MEMBER OF THE WHITE
HOUSE COUNSEL TEAM IN
ATTENDANCE.
LISTEN HERE.
>> SO BOTTOM LINE IS, DON IS A
VERY SMART LAWYER.
HE'S ALREADY TESTIFIED.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN OPEN AND
TRANSPARENT IN THE WAY THE TWO
PREVIOUS PRESIDENTS WERE NOT.
SO I EXPECT HIM TO COME BUT I
INSPECTION HIM TO INSIST ON
HAVING PEOPLE BEHIND HIM THAT
CAN ADVISE HIM AS TOHEN
ANSWER A QUESTION WHEN A
PRIVILEGE NIGHT BE APAu
>> McGAHN HAS BEEN ASKED TO
PR■■UMENTS B MAY 7.THE TESTIMON
SCHEDULED FOR MAY 21.
WE'LL SEE IF GOES.
>> Shepard: JOHN, JARED KUSHNER
IS CLOSE WITH MOHAMMED BIN
SALMAN, THE CROWN PRINCE OF
SAUDI ARABIA.
HE'S ACCUSED BY AMERICAN
INTELLIGENCE AND OTHERS OF
ORDERING THE MURDER OF■T
WASHINGTON POST" COLUMNIST JAMAL
KHAISHOGGI.■÷USHNER H SAY
>> HE DI NOT THAT AT
ALL.
LET ME GIVE YOU THE QUOTE OF
WHAT HE SAID.
HE SAID LOOK, I'M NOT GOING TO
DISPUTE AMERICAN INTELLIGENCE
SERVICES RECOMMENDATIONS.
I'M ALSO NOT GOIO TALK ABOUTANY.
KUSHNER WAS IN■TADH ON■=■=
FEBRUARY 26 AND MET WITH
MOHAMMED BIN■=■=■=■=■=■= SALMAN
NUMBER OF DNT ISSUES.
AT THE■T■T■T■÷■÷A÷A÷■÷A÷■÷A÷■÷A
MURDER HAS AFFECTED HIS■u■÷AMME
■= OTHER SAUDI■= LEADERS
OR ADVICE HE MIGHT HAVE
GIVEN BIN SALMAN.
KUSHNER SAID THE ADVICE I GAVE
WAS TO BE AS TRANSPARENT
POSSIBLE AND WE HAVE TO MAKE■=■.
IT'S NOT THE FIRST TIMA= GAVE
BTR■=A=T.
IN OCTOBER, AS THE ITIRWAYHEATI
SECURITY, JOHN BOLTON, TALKED TO
MBS AND ASKED HIM TO DO THAT.
>> Shepard: THANKS.
SOURCES TELL FOX NEWS THAT THE
FORMER VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN
WILL ANNOUNCE THIS THURSDAY THAT
HE IS RUNNING FOR THE WHITE
HOUSE AND MAKE HIS FIRST
APPEARANCE AS AN OFFICIAL
CANDIDATE NEXT WEEK ON MONDAY IN
PITTSBURGH.
PETER DOOCY REPORTING.
LIVE IN WASHINGTON.
PETER?
>> JOE BIDEN IS SET TO BECOME
2020'S 20th CANDIDATE.
HE WILL EXPLAIN WHY HE'S THE
BEST BET TO TOPPLE TRUMP.
HE HEADS TO PENNSYLVANIA, WHICH
TRUMP WON FOR A CAMPAIGN EVENT
AT A UNION HALL IN PITTSBURGH ON
MONDAY.
HE PLANS TO QUICKLY GO PUBLIC
WITH A LONG LIST OF HIGH PROFILE
ENDORSEMENTS.
THERE'S NO INDICATION THAT
BARACK OBAMA WHO HE SERVES AS
V.P. IS READY TO BACK BIDEN.
THE 76-YEAR-OLD FLIRTED WITH A
CAMPAIGN IN 2016 AS HILLARY
CLINTON STRUGGLED AND NEVER
ANNOUNCED ANYTHING AND
CONTINUING GRIEVING IF LOSS OF
HIS SON IN PRIVATE, THIS WILL BE
BIDEN'S THIRD OFFICIAL BID.
THE FIRST IN 1988,
HE BOUGHED OUT BEFORE THE
CAUCUSES AMID A PLAGIARISM.
THE NEXT TIME HE RAN, HE BOUGHED
OUT AFTER A POOR SHOWING IN THE
IOWA CAUCUSES.
BOWDEN HAS BEEN ACCUSED OF
MAKING WOMEN FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE
WITH TOUCHING AND KISSING.
NOBODY ACCUSED HIM OF SEXUAL
ASSAULT AND THE ALLEGATIONS
DON'T APPEAR TO HAVE IMPACTED
HIS EFFORT IN ANY WAY.
THERE'S QUESTIONS ABOUT COMMENTS
BIDEN MADE IN UKRAINE WHERE HE
JOKED ABOUT PRESSURING A
UKRAINIAN OFFICIAL THAT WAS
INVESTIGATING A COMPANY HIS SON
WORKED FOR.
IT'S ALL PART OF A DECADES LONG
REPORT THAT IS ABOUT TO BE
RE-VISITED.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: THANKS.
THE DEBATE ABOUT TRYING TO
IMPEACH PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
SPILLED OVER IN THE CAMPAIGN
TRAIL.
THE 2020 DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES
GOT QUESTIONS ABOUT WHETHER THEY
SUPPORT CONGRESS MOVING FORWARD
WITH IMPEACHMENT LAST NIGHT ON
TOWN HALL MEETINGS ON CNN.
NANCY PELOSI IS URGING HER PARTY
TO HOLD OFF ON THOSE EFFORTS AND
FOCUS ON INVESTIGATIONS INTO THE
PRESIDENT, HIS CAMPAIGN AND
BUSINESSES TO AS SHE PUTS IT TO
SEE WHERE THE FACTS LEAD.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO SOURCES
BRIEFED ON A CONFERENCE CALL LED
BY SPEAKER PELOSI LAST NIGHT.
PETER, SOUNDS LIKE SHE'S TESTING
THE WATERS WITH THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE BEFORE JUMPING IN HEAD
FIRST.
>> AND SO ARE MULTIPLE DEMOCRATS
HOPING TO REPLACE PRESIDENT
TRUMP AT THE BALLOT BOX WHO ARE
ADVOCATING FOR CONGRESS TO
IMPEACHMENT BEFORE THAT.
>> I BELIEVE THAT EVERY PERSON
IN THE SENATE AND THE HOUSE
OUGHT TO HAVE TO VOTE AND TO SAY
EITHER YEAH, THAT'S OKAY WITH
ME.
YEAH, LET HIM STEP IN THE WAY HE
DID WHEN HE TOLD THE WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL TO GO FIRE MUELLER.
>> I THINK WE HAVE VERY GOOD
REASON TO BELIEVE THERE'S AN
INVESTIGATION THAT HAS BEEN
CONDUCTED WHICH HAS PRODUCED
EVIDENCE THAT TELLS US THAT THIS
PRESIDENT ABOUT HIS
ADMINISTRATION ENGAGED IN
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
I BELIEVE CONGRESS SHOULD TAKE
THE STEP TOWARDS IMPEACHMENT.
>> JOE BIDEN SAID HE DIDN'T WANT
ANYBODY TALKING ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT UNTIL AFTER THE
MUELLER REPORT.
WE'LL SEE IF HE CHANGED HIS MIND
SOON, SHEP.
>> Shepard: PETER, THERE'S THE
DEBATE ON FELONS VOTING.
BERNIE SANDERS DEFENDING HIS
POSITION THAT ALL FELONS SHOULD
BE ALLOWED TO VOTE.
>> HE TOLD A CROWD FROM NEW
ENGLAND THAT HE THINKS THE
BOSTON BOMBER SHOULD VOTE FROM
PRISON, TOO, A FEW DAYS AFTER
THE REGION MARKED THE SIXTH
ANNIVERSARY OF THE MARATHON
ATTACKS.
>> MY FOLLOW QUESTION GOES TO
THIS LIKE YOU'RE WRITING AN
OPPOSITION AD AGAINST YOU.
YOU THINK THE BOSTON MARATHON
BOMBER SHOULD VOTE NOT AFTER HE
PAYS HIS DEBT TO SOCIETY BUT
WHILE HE'S IN JAIL.
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
>> CHRIS, I THINK I HAVE WRITTEN
MANY 30-SECOND OPPOSITION ADS
THROUGHOUT MY LIFE.
>> LATER AGREED, SHE SAID SHE
SUPPORTS HAVING A CONVERSATION
ABOUT THAT.
>> PETER DOOCY LIVE IN
WASHINGTON.
THANKS.
>> Shepard: BIG NEWS FROM THE
CAMPAIGN TRAIL.
FOX NEWS WILL HOST A TOWN HALL
WITH PETE BUTTIGIEG.
THE MAYOR OF SOUTH BEND,
INDIANA.
THE DATE, SUNDAY MAY 19, 7:00
EASTERN TIME, 6:00 CENTRAL.
CHRIS WALLACE WILL MODERATE LIVE
FROM CLAREMONT, NEW HAMPSHIRE.
PETE BUTTIGIEG AND CHRIS WALLACE
MAY 19.
PROSECUTORS OFTEN GO AFTER DRUG
DEALERS AND TRY TO TARGET THEIR
SUPPLIERS.
THOSE AT THE TOP.
NOW THEY'RE A PLAYING THE EXACT
SAME PROCEDURE TO A
PHARMACEUTICAL COMPANY AND ITS
EXECUTIVES.
THE FORM OF ITS KIND CRIMINAL
CHARGES IN THE OPIOID CRISIS
COMING UP.
FIRST, THE FOX URGENT AND THE
NASDAQ RIGHT NOW IS THE HIGHEST
IT HAS EVER BEEN.
WELL ON ITS WAY TO A RECORD
CLOSE AT THE END OF TRADING IN
THIS HOUR.
WE'LL WATCH IT CLOSELY AND SEE
IF IT HANGS ON.
OVER ON THE S&P, IT IS SHAPING
UP TO BE A BUZZER BEATER.
IT NEEDS TO CLOSE ABOVE 9,230.
SORRY.
2,930.
WE'RE THERE AT THE MOMENT THAT
COULD BE AN ALL-TIME HIGH AS
WELL.
KEEPING TRACK ON THE MARKETS AND
THE BREAKING NEWS AS OUR?]
REPORTING CONTINUES ON THIS
TUESDAY AFTERNOON.
■■■■■■■■■■■--
When I book at Hilton.com
I get to select my room
from the floor plan...
Free Wi-Fi...
So with Hilton
there is nh.
Yeah the only catch
is I'm never leaving.
No I'm serious,
I live here now.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
We're the Tenney's
and we're USAA members for life.
Call USAA to start saving
on insurance today.
>> Shepard: FOX URGENT.
FOR THE FIRST TIMEL
IVES■■■■■■■■■A@AIIIN CHARGES IN
THE OPIOID CRISIS.
FEDERAL PROSECUTORS SAY A FORMER
DRUG COMPANY CEO INSTRUCTED HIS
STAFF TO IGNORE RED FLAGS,
INCLUDING SUSPICIOUSLY LARGE
ORDERS FROM PHARMACIES THAT
SUPPLY PILL MILLS.
PLACES WHERE PATIENTS COULD GET
MANY MORE PAINKILLERS THAN THEY
NEEDED.
THE FORMER EXECUTIVE'S NAME IS
LARRY DOWD.
HERE'S HIS RETIREMENT
ANNOUNCEMENT.
HE WORKED FOR ROCHESTER DRUG
COOPERATIVE WHICH DISTRIBUTED
OXYCODONE AND FENTANYL.
HIS FORMER CHIEF COMPLIANCE
OFFICER IS ALSO FACING CHARGES.
THE FORMER CEO'S ATTORNEY SAID
THAT MR. DOWD IS BEING FRAYED BY
OTHERS TO COVER UP FOR THEIR
WRONG DOING.
THE GOVERNMENT HAS IT ALL WRONG
AND IS BEING USED AN MANIPULATED
BY PEOPLE LOOKING FOR A
SCAPEGOAT.
DOUD WILL DEFEND THESE CHARGES
TO HIS LAST BREATH AND WILL BE
VINDICATED.
THE COMPANY ITSELF IS ADMITTING
IT "MADE MISTAKES."
ROCHESTER DRUG COOPERATIVE
SPOKESMAN SAID THE COMPANY HAS
REACHED A CRIMINAL AND CIVIL
SETTLEMENT DEAL WITH PROSECUTORS
AGREEING TO PAY A $20 MILLION
FINE AND LAUNCH A COMPLIANCE
PROGRAM.
LET'S TURN TO KATIE.
SHE'S A FORMER FEDERAL
PROSECUTOR AND NOW A CRIMINAL
DEFENSE ATTORNEY.
THE FEDERAL CHARGES ARE NEW, BUT
THE PAY THE PENALTY AND YOU'RE
SCOT-FREE, THIS IS A PART OF A
PATTERN, ISN'T IT?
>> IT ABSOLUTELY IS.
THERE'S BEEN CIVIL ENFORCEMENTS
AGAINST THESE PHARMACEUTICAL
COMPANIES FOR A LONG TIME.
THE CRIMINAL ENFORCEMENT IS A
NEW THING AND PROBABLY LONG
OVERDO YOU FOR THE FOLKS THAT
ARE RESPONSIBLE AT THE TOP END
FOR THIS OPIOID CRISIS.
>> WHAT IS THIS EXECUTIVE AND
HIS COMPLIANCE OFFICER, WHAT ARE
THE TWO OF THEM BEING CHARGED
WITH AND WHAT COULD HAPPEN TO
THEM UPON CONVICTION, IF IT
HAPPENS?
>> THEY'RE BEING CHARGED UNDER
THE CONTROLLED SUBSTANCES ACT,
WHICH ESSENTIALLY PLACES A LOT
OF RESPONSIBILITY ON
DISTRIBUTORS OF DANGEROUS DRUGS
TO ENSURE THAT THEY ARE MAKING
SURE THAT THEIR CUSTOMERS ARE
USING THEM FOR LEGITIMATE
PERSONS.
SO THEY'RE CHARGED WITH
CONSPIRACIES TO ILLEGALLY
DISTRIBUTE THESE SUBSTANCES TO
PHARMACIES THAT THEY NEW HAD RED
FLAGS AND SELLING THESE DRUGS
ELICITLY.
SO FOR THE FOLKS FIGHTING THE
CHARGES, THEY CAN FACE A
SIGNIFICANT AMOUNT OF JAIL TIME.
THERE'S BEEN A SETTLEMENT
AGREEMENT REACHED FOR SOME OF
THE INDIVIDUALS INVOLVED THAT IS
A DEFERRED PROSECUTION.
SO THEY WILL NOT BE IMMEDIATELY
FACING THAT ASSUMING THEY
SUPPLY.
FOR THOSE FIGHTING IT ALL THE
WAY THROUGH, THIS COULD BE
SIGNIFICANT CONSEQUENCES ON THE
CIVIL SIDE AND CRIMINAL SIDE.
>> Shepard: THE CHARGES MIRROR
THE KIND OF CHARGES THAT A DRUG
KINGPIN WOULD FACE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I THINK IT'S VERY LONG OVERDUE.
THERE'S PEOPLE THAT SELL THESE
DRUGS IN SMALL AMOUNTS ON THE
STREETS AND THEY FACE JAIL TIME
WITHOUT QUESTION.
THESE FOLKS AT THE
PHARMACEUTICAL QUESTIONS ARE
DOING ESSENTIALLY THE SAME
THING.
BUT FROM A CORPORATE
PERSPECTIVE.
ON THE DEFENSE SIDE, YOU CAN
LOOK AT IT AND SAY THEY'RE NOT
DIRECTLY DISTRIBUTING.
THEY'RE BEING HELD RESPONSIBLE
FOR OTHER PEOPLE'S ACTIONS.
BUT THAT'S PART OF ENGAGING IN
BUSINESS AND SELLING A DANGEROUS
PROTECT.
YOU'RE HELD TO A HIGH STANDARD.
THAT'S WHY THEY'RE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THAT, EVEN THOUGH THEY'RE
NOT DIRECTLY SELLING THE DRUGS.
>> THANKS SO MUCH.
I APPRECIATE IT.
THE NEW CHARGES ARE OUT.
WE'LL KEEP YOU UPDATED ON WHAT
HAPPENS NEXT.
NOW, COMING UP, DOZENS OF FOLKS
SAY THAT THEY WERE RECORDED
WHILE GETTING MASSAGED IN THE
SPA IN THE ROBERT KRAFT
PROSTITUTION STING.
THEY SAID THEY DID NOTHING WRONG
AND THEY'RE TRYING TO KEEP THE
VIDEO FROM GOING PUBLIC.
AND ACTRESS LORI LOUGHLINCE IN
four years or thirty-two
years like myself.
One of the benefits
we as a countryans isn
for up to 100% of
your home's value.
So if you need money
for your family,
call NewDay USA.
With Automatic Authority
from the VA,
we can say yes when
banks say no.
Call 1-833-844-6708.
We're Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh
and you may know us from...
Your very first sandwich,
Your mammoth masterpiece.
And...whatever this was.
Because we make our meat
with the good of the deli and
no artificial preservatives.
Make every sandwich count
Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh.
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
What do all these people
have in common, LiMu?
[ guttural grunt ]
Exactly. Nothing!
They're completely
different people.
That's why they
make customized
car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need.
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done it again, LiMu.
[ LiMu grunts ]
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
>> Shepard: AUNT BECKY WANTS TO
SEE THE EVIDENCE.
THE EVIDENCE THE GOVERNMENT H
AGAINST HER IN THE COLLEGE
ADMISSIONS CANDLE.
SHE, OF COURSE, IS THE ACTRESS
LORI LOUGHLIN AND HER FASHION
DESIGNER HUSBAND.
JOINING A DOZEN OTHER DEFENDANTS
ASKING FOR THE FEDS TO TURN IT
OVER, ALL THE EVIDENCE.
THEY CLAIM THEY HAVEN'T SEEN ANY
OF IT AND THEY NEED A CHANCE TO
REVIEW IT.
PROSECUTORS SAY THE FULL HOUSE
STAR AND HER HUSBAND PAID
$500,000 TO BRIBE THEIR
DAUGHTER'S WAY INTO THE
UNIVERSITY OF SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA.
THEY PLEADED NOT GUILTY EARLIER
THIS MONTH.
TRACE GALLAGHER HAS MORE.
>> THE EVIDENCE IS KEY.
LOUGHLIN AND HER HOUSE ARE
FACING MONEY LAUNDERING CHARGES
FOR FUNNELING THE $500,000 BRIBE
THROUGH THE RINGLEADER'S CHARITY
AND THE WIRE FRAUD CHANGES
BECAUSE SOME OF THE MONEY WAS
T IN OUTSIDE THE UNITED
STATES.
THE CHARGES INDICATE THE FEDS
HAVE THINGS LIKE BANK RECORDS,
CASH CHECKS, WIRE TRANSFERS,
ET CETERA.
FOR NOW, LOUGHLIN AND HER
HUSBAND HAVE PLEADED■ GUILTY
BECAUSE THE PLEA DEAL INCLUDES
SIGNIFICANT JAIL TIME UP TO FOUR
YEARS.
THEY INITIALLY PASSED ON A MORE
LENIENT PLEA DEAL AND ANOTHER
CHARGE WAS ADDED.
EXPERTS SAY THE COUPLE'S
ATTORNEYS WILL NEED TO SEE HOW
DAMAGING ANY POTENTIAL EVIDENCE
IS BEFORE DECIDING THE NEXT
MOVE.
LOUGHLIN IS REPORTEDLY CONCERNED
THAT HER DAUGHTERS MIGHT BE
CHARGED AS WILLING PARTICIPANTS
BECAUSE IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
WHEN THEY GOT RECRUITED FOR THE
CREW TEAM THEY DIDN'T THINK
SOMETHING WAS UP.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: NOW BOB SAGET IS
TALKING.
>> HE'S NOT SAYING MUCH.
HE'S WORKED OR "FULL HOUSE" WITH
LOUGHLIN FOR EIGHT YEARS.
WHEN HE WAS ASKED ABOUT THE
COLLEGE SCANDAL, HE SAID "IT'S
PERSONAL AND THAT'S WHERE I'M
KEEPING IT AND THERE'S 30 YEARS
OF LOVE THERE."
MORE THAN THAT.
THAT'S ALL I GOT.
THAT'S A■T■T0T0T0TpT■T■T■T■T T■
PIGEON.
WHILE BOB SAGET SAID LITTLE,
SOME OF HER OTHER FRIENDS SAID
THAT THIS IS PUTTING UNSPEAKABLE
PRESS ON LOUGHLIN BECAUSE
THEY'RE FAIR GAME FOR JOKES AND
MEANS.
SHE'S OUTRAGES SAYING THAT SHE'S
A CHEATER.
IF SHE CUTS A PLEA DEAL, CHEATER
WOULD BE THE APPROPRIATE WORD.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: THANKS, TRACE.
LIVE IN LOS ANGELES.
HIDDEN CAMERAS AT A DAY SPA IN
FLORIDA ARE SAID TO HAVE
REPORTED THE NEW ENGLAND
PATRIOTS OWNER BOB KRAFT AND
OTHERS PAYING FOR SEX.
THAT VIDEO IS PART OF COURT
PROCEEDINGS AND WILL BE RELEASED
TO THE PUBLIC.
HERE'S THE THING.
THERE'S OTHERS THAT CLAIM ALL
THEY DID IS GET A MASSAGE.
THE VIDEO RECORDINGS OF THEIR
MASSAGES AND NOTHING MORE MAY
BECOME PUBLIC AND THEY'RE
FIGHTING TO KEEP THEIR VIDEO
PRIVATE.
HOW MANY PEOPLE WE TALKING ABOUT
HERE?
>> THE COUNT HAS JUMPED FROM 17
TO 31, JOHN AND JANE DOES WHO
SAID THEIR PRIVACY WAS STRIPPED
DOWN WHEN THEY GOT CAUGHT UP IN
THIS.
THE THREE DOZEN MEN WOMEN
ILED THE CLASS ACTION
LAWSUIT ALLEGE PROSECUTORS AND
POLICE UNLAWFULLY VIDEOTAPED
THEM IN A PRIVATE SETTING.
ORCHIDS OF ASIA WAS ONE OF FOUR
SPAS IN AN EIGHT-MONTH
INVESTIGATION WHICH UNCOVERED
PROSTITUTION AT A■/ TOTAL OF FI>
SPAS.
THERE'S BEEN AN■  JOHN GOING LEL
TUG OF WAR WITH PROSECUTORS
SAYING THEY HAD TO RELEASE
VIDEOS UNDER THE FLORIDA
SUNSHINE LAWS.
THE JUDGE RULED THIS AFTERNOON
THE VIDEO WILL NOT BE MADE
PUBLIC FOR NOW SIDING WITH
KRAFT'S ATTORNEYS ARGUING THAT
RELEASING THE VIDEO WOULD HARM
HIS CHANCE FOR A FAIR TRIAL.
KRAFT HAS PLEADED NOT GUILTY.
PROSECUTORS SAID THEY FOUND NO
EVIDENCE OF TRAFFICKING AT THE
DA SPA.
>> Shepard: BUT ANOTHER PERSON
WAS RESTED?
>> YES, MONDAY.
A WOMAN IS 58 YEARS OLD.
POLICE SAY SHE WAS CAUGHT ON
HIDDEN SURVEILLANCE PERFORMING A
SEX ACT ON THE PATRIOTS OWNER.
AFTER WARTS, KRAFT PAID HER AND
THE MANAGER OF THE SPA IN CASH.
ACCORDING TO HER ARREST REPORT,
THE WOMAN WAS CAPTURED ON VIDEO
PERFORMING ILLEGAL SEX ACTS ON
SIX OTHER MEN.
SHE CHARGED OF OFFERING TO
COMMIT PROSTITUTION.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: THANKS, LAURA.
THE CHINESE REPORTEDLY USING
AMERICAN SATELLITES FOR THEIR
OWN BENEFIT.
WE'LL HEAR HOW THEY'RE DOING IT
COMING UP.
PLUS, ISIS CLAIMING
RESPONSIBILITY FOR THEBINGS
INANKA THAT KILLED MORE
THAN 300 PEOPLE AND WOUNDED MORE
THAN 5 OTHERS.
THE COUNTRY'S PRIME MINISTER HAS
A NEW WARNING FOR HIS OWN
PEOPLE.
BUT FIRST, THE NASDAQ ON TRACK
FOR A RECORD CLOSE TODAY.
GERRI WILLIS IS LIVE AT THE
NEW YORK STOCK EXCHANGE.
>> SHEP, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU SAW THE LEVELS THERE.
IF THE NASDAQ CLOSES ABOVE
8,109, IT WILL SET AN ALL-TIME
RECORD.
HIGHEST HIGH EVER.
THAT'S VERY BIG NEWS FOR THE
NASDAQ.
WHAT IS INTERESTING ABOUT THIS,
NORMALLY THE NASDAQ HAS BEEN LED
BY THE FIVE STOCKS, FACEBOOK,
AMAZON.
BUT NOW THE SEMI CONDUCTORS, 5G
WIRELESS.
GIVES AT LOT OF CONFIDENCE TO
INVESTORS.
MEANWHILE, WE'RE LOOKING AT HIGH
EXPECTATIONS FROM FACEBOOK,
MICROSOFT AND AMAZON THIS WEEK.
THAT SHOULD PROPEL THEM FURTHER.
WEAKER VOLUMES.
THIS WON'T LAST FOREVER.
MORE TO COME LATER AS SHEPARD
SMITH CONTINUES AFTER THIS.
♪ ♪
Dealing with psoriatic arthr■■■.
My skin...
it was embarrassing.
The pain and swelling..
The tenderness.
The psoriasis.
I had to find something
that worked on all of this.
I found  COSENTYX.
Now, watch me.
Real people with active
psoriatic arthritis
are getting real relief
with COSENTYX.
It's a different kind
of targeted biologic.
COSENTYX treats more
than just the joint pain
soriat.
It even helps stope
further joint damage.in
if you're
allergic to COSENTYX.
Before starting, get
checked for tuberculosis.
[ased risk
of inf
and lowered ability to
c fight them may occur.s.
Tell your doctor about
an infection or symptoms.
If your inflammatory
bowel disease symptoms
develop or worsen,
or if you've had a vaccine
or plan to.
Serious allergic
reactions may occur.
■■
I got real relief.
I got clearer skin
and feel better.
Get real relief
Now,/
with COSENTYX.
At Carvana,
we have only one standard
when it comes to the quality
of our cars: The highest.
It's why only 1 in 10 cars
we look at
qualify to sell on our site.
If it's been
in a reported accident,
we won't sell it.
And at our
state-of-the-art facilities
our ASE certified mechanics
roll up their sleeves
■■
Inspecting, dialing-in,
and fine tuning every single car
inside and out,
bringing all of it up
to our high standards.
By the time we're done,
our cars are
beyond "certified."
They're Carvana certified.
So whether you have it delivered
or pick it up,
we do it all
so you can rest easy.
You might take something
for your heart...
or joints.
But do you take something
for your brain.
With an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish,
Prevagen has been shown
in clinical trials
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
My insurance rates are probably
gonna double.
But dad, you've got
ALLSTATE.
WITH ACCIDENT FORGIVENESS
THEY GUARANTEE YOUR RATES
WON'T GO UP
JUST BECAUSE OF AN ACCIDENT.
Smart kid.
INDEED.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
>> Shepard: THE SUPREME COURT
HEARING ARGUMENTS ON WHETHER THE
2020 CENSUS SHOULD ASK PEOPLE IF
THEY'RE LEGAL CITIZENS OF THE
UNITED STATES.
THE CITIZENSHIP QUESTION HAS NOT
ARED SINCE 50.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IS
FIGHTING TO BRING IT BACK
ARGUING IT WILL HELP■■■■K■K■■■■■
VOTING
CRITICS SAY THE QUESTION COULD
ACTUALLY DISCOURAGE MILLIONS OF
IMMIGRANTS LEGAL AND OTHERWISE
FOR PARTICIN THE CENSUS,
WHICH LEAD TO AN INACCURATE
POPULATION COUNT AND RESULT IN
SOME AREAS LOSING SEATS IN
CONGRESS AND LOSING FEDERAL
FUNDING.
ACCORDING TO OUR TEAM IN THE
COURTROOM, THE ARGUMENTS WERE AT
TIMES HEATED.
SELF JUSTICES INTERCEPTED
COUNSEL SEVERAL TIMES.
THE HIGH COURT'S FIRST LATINA
JUSTICE SAID THERE'S NO DOUBT
MANY IN THE IMMIGRANTMUNITY
WOULD SKIP THE CENSUS I
CITIZENSHIP QUES ONIT.■
JOHN ROBERTS■ THE SURVEY
HAS ASKED DEMOGRAPHIC QUESTIONS
IN THE PAST, QUESTIONS INCLUDING
GENDER AND AGE.
OFFICIALS AT THE CENSUS BUREAU
SAID THEY NEED A DECISION ON THE
CITIZEN SIP QUESTION BY THE
MONTH OF JUNE SO THAT THEY CAN
START PRINTING THE FORMS.
CHINA IS TAKING ADVANTAGE OF
AMERICAN-MADE SATELLITES USING
THOSE SATELLITES FOR EVERYTHING
FROM SPREADING CHINESE STATE
MESSAGES TO HELPING CHINESE
POLICE CRACK DOWN ON
ANTI-GOVERNMENT DEMONSTRATIONS.
ANALYSTS WARN BEIJING'S MILITARY
COULD USE THE UNITED STATES
TECHNOLOGY TO GUIDE CHINESE
MISSILES TO THEIR TARGETS.
ALL OF THAT ACCORDING TO AN
INVESTIGATION BY THE "WALL
STREET JOURNAL."
THE JOURNAL'S PARENT COMPANY AND
FOX NEWS SHARE COMMON OWNERSHIP.
THERONES THAT BAN CHINA
FROM BUYING U.S.-BIT SATELLITES.
ACCORDING TO THE REPORTING OF
THE JOURNAL, THERE'S NO LAW
REGULATING USE OF OUR SATELLITES
FREQUENCIES.
SO CHINA IS ESSENTIALLY RENTING
OUR SERVICES IN SPACE AND COULD
POTENTIALLY USE THEM AGAINST US.
LET'S BRING IN KATE O'KEEFE, A
REPORTER FOR THE "WALL STREET
JOURNAL."
KATE, THANK YOU.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> FOR THOSE THAT UNDERSTAND
SATELLITE TECHNOLOGY, IT'S LIKE
A BUNCH OF WINDOWS ON THE
SATELLITE.
YOU CAN USE THEM TO BOUNCE
THINGS OFF.
INFORMATION AND OTHERWISE.
WHAT EXACTLY ARE THE CHINESE
CAPABLE OF DOING WITH OUR
SATELLITES?
WHAT WE FOUND IN THIS
INVESTIGATION IS THAT CHINA IS
BASICALLY MAKING USE OF A FLEET
OF U.S.-MADE SATELLITES TO
ACHIEVE STRATEGIC GOALS THAT RUN
COUNTER TO U.S. FOREIGN POLICY.
IN ONE CASE, WE FOUND CHINA WAS
USING SOME OF THESE SATELLITES
TO CONNECT CHINESE MILITARY
UNCONTESTED OUTPOSTS IN THE
SOUTH CHINA SEA.
IN OTHER CASES, WE FOUND THE
SATELLITES WERE BEING USED BY
TO BOLSTER THEIR POLICE
FORCES IN REGIONS LIKE TIBET
WHERE INTERNATIONAL GROUPS HAVE
DOCUMENTED HUMAN RIGHTS ABUSES.
>> HAS THE UNITED STATES WEIGHED
IN ON THIS?
>> SO ONE INTERESTING THING
ABOUT THIS PROJECT THAT WE
LEARNED IS THAT ALL OF THIS
ACTUALLY APPEARS TO BE LEGAL
BECAUSE THE U.S. BANS AMERICAN
COMPANIES FROM DIRECTLY SELLING
SATELLITES TO CHINA.
THERE'S NO REGULATION ON HOW THE
SATELLITE IS USED IN SPACE.
SO THAT'S A REALLY WORK AROUND
THAT CHINA HAS FOUND THAT HAS
ENABLED THEM TO TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THIS U.S. TECHNOLOGY WITHOUT
ACTUALLY BUYING IT.
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT FOR CHINA.
THEIR SATELLITE TECHNOLOGY IS
INFERIOR TO U.S. TECHNOLOGIES.
>> Shepard: UNDERSTANDING THE
LAW, HAS THE UNITED STATES
COMMENTED ON THE FACT THAT THIS
IS HAPPENING?
DO WE KNOW IF THE U.S. WAS
AWARE?
>> U.S. OFFICIALS HAVE BEEN
AWARE OF THIS GENERAL DYNAMIC
BECAUSE THEY HAVE APPROVED THE
EXPORT LICENSES FOR THESE
COMPANIES.
>> Shepard: IT'S A FASCINATING
ARTICLE.
KATE O'KEEFE FOR THE "WALL
STREET JOURNAL," OUR CORPORATE
COUSIN.
YOU CAN READ IT NOW AT WSJ.COM.
THANKS.
THE PRIME MINISTER OF SRI LANKA
IS WARNING THAT MORE EXPLOSIVES
AND MORE ATTACKERS ARE STILL OUT
THERE AFTER SUICIDE BOMBERS
KILLED MORE THAN 320 PEOPLE ON
EASTER SUNDAY.
ISIS NOW CLAIMING RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THE BOMBINGS.
SRI LANKAN OFFICIALS SAY THEY
HAD SUSPECTED LINKS TO THE
RROR GROUP.
THE COUNTRY'S DEFENSE MINISTER
SUGGESTS THAT THE ATTACKS WERE
IN RESPONSE TO LAST MONTH'S
MOSQUE ATTACKS IN NEW ZEALAND.
HE DIDN'T OFFER EVIDENCE TO
SUPPORT THAT.
MORE IN JUST A MOMENT.
FIRST, TAKE LOOK AT THIS VIDEO
NEW TO IT.
IT SHOWS THE SUSPECTED BOMBER
WALKING OVER TO THE
ST. SEBASTIAN CHURCH NORTH OF
COLUMBO.
THAT IS THE CHURCH THAT YOU JUST
SAW.
YOU CAN SEE HE'S WEARING A
BACKPACK HERE.
AS HE MAKES HIS W■4 TO THE
CHURCH PACKED WITH LOTS OF
PEOPLE.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE ATTACKS
KILLED PEOPLE FROM 12 COUNTRIES
AND 45 ■■■.
A SPOKESPERSON CONFIRMED FOUR
AMERICANS ARE AMONG THE DEAD.
SRI LANKA ON THE STATE OF THE
EMERGENCY ALLOWING THE MILITARY
TO ENFORCE ITS WARTIME POWERS.
OFFICIALS CAN SEARCH PROPERTY
WITHOUT A WARRANT.
THERE'S A CURFEW IN EFFECT.
NO MOVEMENT OVERNIGHT.
EVEN BEFORE CURFEW, A REPORTER
FOUND THE STREETS OF SRI LANKA'S
CAPITOL NEARLY DESERTED.
>> A LOT OF FEAR IN SRI LANKA.
A LOT OF SECURITY INCLUDING WHAT
YOU SEE AT THIS HOTEL.
THAT'S THE CASE ACROSS THE CITY
OF COLUMBO, SRI LANKA'S CAPITOL.
>> Shepard: THE PRIME MINISTER
SAYS PEOPLE WILL LIKELY LOSE
THEIR JOBS BECAUSE OF
INTELLIGENCE FAILURES.
CATHERINE HERRIDGE REPORTING ON
ALL OF THIS LIVE FROM
WASHINGTON.
CATHERINE?
>> WE'VE HAD SEVERAL CLAIMING
RESPONSIBILITY THROUGHOUT THE
DAY, BEGINNING WITH THE TERROR'S
OFFICIAL NEWS AGENCY.
THAT READS --
THIS STATEMENT DID NOT OFFER
EVIDENCE TO BACK UP THE CLAIM
AND THERE'S NO DIRECT EVIDENCE
THE TERROR GROUP WAS INVOLVED.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO NOTE UNLIKE
AL-QUAIDA, ISIS HAS MADE FALSE
CLAIMS IN THE PAST.
ABOUT THREE HOURS LATER, A
SECOND CLAIM OF RESPONSIBILITY
CAME IN LISTING SEVEN
INDIVIDUALS AND IDENTIFYING THEM
AS BOMBERS AS WELL AS THEIR
ALLEGED TARGETS.
FINALLY AN HOUR AGO, ANOTHER
CLAIM INCLUDING ALLEGED VIDEO OF
THE ATTACKERS SWEARING LOYALTY
TO ISIS'S LEADER WHOSE
WHEREABOUTS ARE UNKNOWN IN IRAQ.
TOM JOHNSON WRITES ABOUT
AL-QUAIDA AND TOLD FOX NEWS THAT
THE VIDEO IS SIGNIFICANT BECAUSE
IT MAY BE THE ATTACKS WERE MORE
THAN INSPIRED BY ISIS.
>> Shepard: CATHERINE, A
SRI LANKAN OFFICIAL SAID THIS
WAS A RETALIATION FOR THE
SHOOTING AT MOSQUES IN
NEW ZEALAND.
DO YOU HAVE DETAILS?
>> THE PRELIMINARY INVESTIGATIO
ATTACKS■ WERE RETALIATION FOR T
NEW ZEALAND BOMBINGS AT MOSQUES.
THE LAST 48  ATT ■■■/97S/■/
BEARS THE HALL M■ Np■>G>■>ISIS .
IT WAS ATTACKS ON PLACES OF■
WORSHIP, TOURIST SITES WHICH
DAMAGE THE ECONOMY.
THIS MORNING THE SRI LANKAN
PRIME MINISTER SEEMED TO QUALIFY
THOSE DEFENSE SECRETARY'S
COMMENTS SAYING IT WAS POSSIBLE
THE ATTACKS WERE LINKED AND
EMPHASIZED THE LIKELY ROLE OF
EXTERNAL FORCES.
>> WE HAVE NEWS COMING IN FROM
CAIRO THAT IS SUPERIOR HAS
CLAIMED RESPONSIBILITY.
ALL THAT WE KNEW EARLIER.
>> NEW ZEALAND'S PRIME MINISTER
HAS BEEN RELUCTANT TO SUPPORT
THIS CONNECTION SAYING THE
INVESTIGATION IS IN ITS EARLIER
STAGES AND HAS NOT SEEN
INTELLIGENCE THAT SUPPORT THAT
CONCLUSION OR THE THAT LINK,
SHEP.
>> Shepard: THANKS, CATHERINE.
ANOTHER LAWSUIT IN THE CASE
INVOLVING THE EMPIRE ACTOR
JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
THIS TIME FROM THE TWO BROTHERS
THAT SAY THEY HELPED SMOLLETT
STAGE THE ATTACK ON HIMSELF.THA.
value.             s
Thank You, Admiral.
So if you need money for your
family,
call NewDay USA.■
Need cash?
At NewDay, veteran homeowners
can get
$54,000 dollars or more
to consolidate hig■÷dit
card debt
and lower their payments by $600
every month.■÷■÷
0G$ç)FMNnDv-B0.H#ú$DP;n.úUn&>Xqi
Diaper Duty.
It's not the highlight
of fatherhood.
But I'd rather be here
with my little man
than anywhere with migraine.
"I am here."
And I aim to say that more.
Aimovig...
a preventive treatment for
migraine in adults...
reduces the number of monthly
migraine days.
For some, that number can be cut
in half or more.
The most common side effects
are pain,
redness or swelling at the
injection site and constipation.
Aim to be there more.
Talk to your doctor
about Aimovig.
With tough food, your dentures
may slip and fall.
Fixodent Ultra-Max Hold
gives you the strongest hold
ever
to lock your dentures.
So now you can eat tough food
without worry.
Fixodent and forget it.
I have a vision
correction number,
But I'm more than a number.
When I'm not sharing ideas
with my colleagues
I'm defending my kingdom.
My Essilor lenses offer more
than vision correction
with three innovative
technologies
For my ultimate in vision
Clarity
And Protection
Together in a single lens:
The Essilor Ultimate
Lens Package.
So, I can do more
of what I love!
Buy two pairs of
Essilor's best lenses
and get a $100 back instantly.
See more. Do more. Essilor
>> Shepard: THE TWO BROTHERS
THAT SAY JUSSIE SMOLLETT PAID
THEM TO STAGE A HATE CRIME
ATTACK ARE SUING THE ACTOR'S
ATTORNEYS FOR DEFAMATION.
I SAID THEIR NAMES WRONG BEFORE
THE COMMERCIAL.
THEY'RE THEU%■áNN■
SMOLLETT'S LEGAL TEAM HAS
INSISTED THE ATTACK WAS REAL
EVEN THOUGH THE OSUNDAIRO
BROTHERS CONFESSED TO POLICE AND
TOLD A GRAND JURY THAT SMOLLETT
ORCHESTRATED THE WHOLE THING.
THE BROTHER'S LAWSUIT CLAIMS
THAT SMOLLETT'S LAWYERS MADE
FALSE AND VICIOUS REMARKS ABOUT
THEM INCLUDING THEY WORE WHITE
FACE WHEN THEY ATTACKED THE
ACTOR.
>> WE WANT TO END THESE
MALICIOUS ATTACKS AND ENSURE
THAT THOSE RESPONSIBLE FOR
CONTINUING TO DESTROY THE
REPUTATION OF THE CHICAGO POLICE
DEPARTMENT, THE CITY OF CHICAGO
AND THAT OF THE OSUNDAIRO
BROTHERS ARE HELD ACCOUNTABLE.
>> Shepard: SMOLLETT HAS
ADMITTED THAT HE DID WRITE A
CHECK TO THE BROTHERS, BUT HE
CLAIMS THAT CHECK WAS FOR A
NUTRITION AND WORKOUT SERVICE.
MIKE TOBIN REPORTING FROM
CHICAGO.
WE JUST HEARD FROM SMOLLETT'S
ATTORNEY ABOUT THIS LAWSUIT,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH, MARK GARRAGOS CAME OUT
SWINGING.
HERE'S THE STATEMENT.
>> NOW, THE BROTHERS DO ADMIT
THAT THEY EXECUTED THE ATTACK
BUT CLAIM THE HOAX WAS CONCEIVED
AND DIRECTED BY JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
THEIR ATTORNEYS SAY THEY'RE JUST
TRYING TO CLEAR THEIR NAME.
>> THEY WERE ASKED TO DO
SOMETHING BY A FRIEND THEY
TRUSTE AT THE END OF THE
DAY, THE FRIEND NAMED THE TRUTH.
>> THE SUIT DOES NOT NAME JUSSIE
SMOLLETT.
IT CLAIMS THE OSUNDAIRO BROTHERS
THAT SAID THAT THINGS THAT
WEREN'T TRUE AND THAT THEY
EXECUTED A HATE CRIME OR WORE
WHITE FACE.
THE BROTHERS CLAIM THEIR
PERSONAL TRAINING BUSINESS WAS
DAMAGED, THEY SUFFERED EMOTIONAL
DISTRESS AND THAT IS ACCORDING
TO THE SUIT, SHEP.
>> Shepard: MIKE, WHAT SORT OF
DAMAGES ARE THEY SEEKING?
>> AN UNSPECIFIED NOTHING.
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR PUNITIVE
DAMAGES AND THEY WANT THE
GERAGOS TEAM TO PICK UP THEIR
LEGAL COSTS.
>> Shepard: THANKS.
IMAGINE YOU HAIL A TAXI, THE CAR
PULLS OVER AND THERE'S NOBODY
TESLA'SEO ELON MUSK SAYS
THAT'S HIS GOAL FOR NEXT YEAR.
TESLAS EVERYWHERE WITH NO
DRIVERS.
UP NEXT, THE DETAILS ON HIS
PLANNED FLEET OF ROBO TAXIS.
HUMAN DRIVERS, NOT INCLUDED.
BUT FIRST, THIS JUST IN TO FOX
NEWS.
YOU MAY KNOW HIS FACE BUT MAY --
MAY NOT KNOW THE FACE BUT KNOW
HIS NAME.
HIS NAME, HE'S ONE OF THE
FOUNDERS OF THE TAX PREPARATION
COMPANY HENRY BLOCK DIED.
HE DIED OF NATURAL CAUSES IN
KANSAS CITY.
difficult job.
Failure is not an option.
More than half of employees
across the country
bring financial stress to work.
If you're stressed out
financially at home,
you're going to be too worried
to be able to do a good job.
I want to be able to offer all
of the benefits
that keep them satisfied.
It is the people that is really
the only asset that you have.
Put your employees on a path
to financial wellness
with Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
---
Please. There must be something
you can do.
Son. Your heart's not
strong enough.
My heart is as strong as any.
Uncover your family history,
from over 10 billion historical
records.
Get started for FREE at
ancestry.com
♪♪
This is the family who booked
the flight,
who saved by adding a hotel,
which led to new adventures,
♪
that captured their
imaginationsO
♪♪
and turned moments into
memories.
With flights, hotelsactine
for your Florida vacation,
Expedia has everything
you need to go.
"Curiouser and
curiouser,"
said Alice.
“The rabbit-hole
went straight on
like a tunnel for some way.”
"I've seen a cat without a gri,
but a grin without a cat.”
Hey, Mercedes, end audio.
Change lighting to soft blue.
The completely reimagined
2020 GLE.
With intelligent voice control
and available third row.
Your adventure awaits at the
Mercedes-Benz Spring Event
but hurry the event
ends April 30th.
>> Shepard: NOW PROFESSIONAL
MOUNTAIN CLIMBERS ARE HELPING TO
PUT TARPS OVER NOTRE DAME ■I■I■I
CATHEDRA
■IS OF THE ROOF ARE OBVIOUSLY
■■■■■■i■
DESTROYED IT.çPARIS IS EXPECTINS
WEEK.
SO OFFICIALS SAY PROTECTING WHAT
IS LEFT OF THE CENTURIES OLD
BUILDING IS THE HIGHEST PRIORITY
RIGHT NOW.
INVESTIGATORS ARE STILL LOOKING
INTO THE FIRE.
THEY HAVE SAID IT'S LIKELY AN
ACCIDENT.
LIKELY RELATED TO RENOVATION
WORK.
THE BILLIONAIRE ENTREPRENEUR
ELON MUSK IS PROMISING TO ROLL
OUT DRIVERLESS TAXIS NEXT YEAR.
MORE THAN A MILLION TESLAS WILL
BE ON THE ROAD AND ABLE TO DRIVE
BY THEMSELVES.
NEXT YEAR.
HE ALSO SAYS HE WANTS TO MAKE IT
POSSIBLE FOR YOU TO PUSH A
BUTTON ON YOUR SMART PHONE TO
PUT YOUR CAR TO WORK.
KRISTINA PARTSINEVELOS IS
REPORTING LIVE.
I THOUGHT THIS WAS YEARS AND
YEARS AWAY?
>> I THOUGHT YOU EMPHASIZED IT
PERFECTLY.
LITERALLY NEXT WE'RE WE'LL HAVE
THE DRIVERLESS CARS AND WILL BE
SAY.
THAT'S WHAT ELON MUSK SAID.
HE HOSTED AN INVESTOR DAY
YESTERDAY TRYING TO WOO
INVESTORS AND HE SPOKE TO
SEVERAL OF THEM.
LISTEN TO WHAT HE HAD TO SAY
ABOUT THIS BOLD PROMISE.
>> WE HAVE CARS BEING PRODUCED
RIGHT NOW AND HAVE EVERYTHING
NECESSARY FOR FULL SELF-DRIVING.
ALL YOU NEED TO DO IS IMPROVE
THE SOFTWARE.
>> THERE YOU HAVE IT.
JUST THE SOFTWARE.
IT'S A COMPLETE OF CARS CALLED
ROBO TAXIS.
HE'S MADE SOME BOLD PROMISES IN
THE PAST.
IN 2018, TESLA PROMISED 500,000
VEHICLES.
THEY PRODUCED AFTER THAT.
LAST YEAR, THEY SAID 10,000
MODEL 3S PER WEEK BUT THEY
HAVEN'T CUT CLOSE TO THAT
NUMBER.
SO YOU HAVE TESLA AS A HOLD
MAKING BOLD PROMISES AND
INCLUDING THEY CREATED THE
WORLD'S FASTEST COMPUTER FOR
DRIVERLESS VEHICLES.
WE'LL SEE IF THAT'S TRUE.
>> Shepard: HOW ARE INVESTORS
AND TESLA'S STOCK REACTING TO
THIS?
>> VERY GOOD.
ITS A BIG BOUNCY BALL FOR TESLA.
YESTERDAY AFTER INVESTORS MET,
THEY WEREN'T SOLD ON THE ROBO
FLEET.
YOU HAVE SOME INVESTORS TELL FOX
BUSINESS THERE'S TOO MANY
PROMISES AND TOO SHORT 0 TIME.
THEY'RE CONCERNED ABOUT DEMAND
AND DELIVERY.
IF WE THINK OF THE TIMING, YOU
HAVE THEM COMING OUT MONDAY,
TALKING ABOUT HOW GREAT THE
FUTURE WILL BE AND THE EARNINGS
ARE EXPECTED TOMORROW ON
WEDNESDAY.
WE'RE EXPECTING A LOSS DUE TO A
DROP IN SALES.
>> Shepard: KRISTINA
PARTSINEVELOS LIVE.
THANK YOU.
A QUICK CHECK OF THE DOW NOW.
IT'S NOT THE BIGGEST NEWS OF THE
DAY.
THE DOW IS UP.
THE FINAL BELL WILL RING IN JUST
A MOMENT.
139 ■■■
HE THE BIG NEWS.
THE NASDAQ, THE ALL-TIME HIGH ON
THE NASDAQ IS 1,809.
WE'RE ABOUT TO BLOW THAT OUT OF