[LAUGHTER]
SO AFTER A HARD WORKOUT YOU CAN
CELEBRATE WITH A BREW, BOTTOMS
UP.
THAT IS THE MAIN COMPANY THERE.
>> Greg: THAT IS A TERRIBLE
NAME.
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE A SUFFER
FAST.
NEVER MISS AN EPISODE OF "THE
FIVE."
"SPECIAL REPORT" IS UP NEXT.
>> Bret: WHERE CAN I GET ONE
OF THOSECKSUIT'S?
S ALERT.
THE WHITE HOUSERUMP=■=■= REPORT=
DEMOCRAT PREPARES TO ENTER THE=D
RACE.
■=■=■=■= I■=■=■=■=■=■=■=■=■=■=■T
■=■=HE MARKETS HAVE TAKEN■=■= TT
IN STR■=
TONIGHT YOUR 401(K) IS PROBABLY
A LOT HEALTHIER THAN IT HAS BEEN
IN A WILD.
A BIG DAY ON WALL STREET AS THE
S&P 500 AND THE NASDAQ CLOSED AT
RECORD HIGHS, COVERING ALL THE
GROUND THEY LOST YESTERDAY LATE
LAST YEAR.
THE DELL HAD A STRONG
PERFORMANCE AS WELL NETTING 145
AND CLOSING IN ON ITS OWN
RECORD.
THE S&P 500 WAS■= AND THE■=■=■=
THE MARKET IS
BETTER-THAN-EXPECTED FROM
NU■ AN■ ■1 TOD■ EVENING.
>> THE MARKET CONTINUES IN 2019,
SURPRISING MONEY THAN THOUGHT IT
WAS COMING TO AN END.
ESPECIALLY AFTER A DISMAL
DECEMBER, THE S&P 500 SURPASSING
ITS LAST RECORD HIGH STRUCK IN
SEPTEMBER LAST YEAR.
IT IS ALSO THE 81ST RECORD UNDER
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THE NASDAQ HITTING 96, 90 RECORD
AND THUS A ADMINISTRATION.
>> HE ENDED THE WAR ON BUSINESS.
HE IS UNDER THE WAR ON SUCCESS.
HE BELIEVES STRONGLY THAT IF YOU
DO WELL AND SUCCEED YOU SHOULD
BE REWARDED, NOT PUNISHED.
>> WHAT HAS BEEN POWERING THE
RALLY?
THE FEDERAL RESERVE'S LINGERING
TELMEX TINGLING THAT THE BANK IS
NOT LIKELY TO RAISE RATES THIS
YEAR, SIDES OF EACH RADIO WILL
BE SIGNED SOON AND COMPANY'S
EARNINGS CONTINUE TO DEFY
GRAVITY AND THAT IS DESPITE A
DROP IN CORPORATE PROFITS THE
FIRST THREE MONTHS OF THE YEAR.
BIG TECH HAS BEEN ONE OF THE
MOST FAVORITE TRADE SO FAR WITH
BIG GAINS FOR AMAZON, APPLE,
NETFLIX AND MICROSOFT.
VIRTUALLY EVERY SECTOR HAS SEEN
AN ADVANCE WITH STOCKS BIG AND
SMALL JOINING IN ON THE RALLY.
A STRONG STOCK MARKET AND A
GROWING U.S. ECONOMY, THE
PRESIDENT DOESN'T GET ENOUGH
MEDIA ATTENTION.
HE TWEETED, "IN THE OLDEN DAYS
IF YOU ARE PRESIDENT AND YOU HAD
A GOOD ECONOMY YOU ARE BASICALLY
IMMUNE FROM CRITICISM."
THIS WEEK IS ANOTHER BIG TEST
WITH TECH GIANTS REPORTING
RESULTS TOMORROW.
THAT IS A BIG ONE, ECONOMIST
FORECAST BETWEEN 1.5% YOU MAY BE
2.5% GROWTH, AG BOUNCE
BACK AFTER A GOVERNMENT SHU
TO■=■=■=■=■= YEAR.
>> B SUS LEE INNEW YORKNK■8■8■88
THEY FREQUENT TARGET OF THE
PRESIDENT'S WRATH BUT IS ALSO A
PRIMARY COMMUNICATION TOOL FOR
HIM AND CASE IN POINT.
HE JUST TWEETED ABOUT THE
MEETING LAST HOUR, "GREAT
MEETING AT THE WHITE HOUSE."
LOTS OF SUBJECTS DISCUSSED
REGARDING THEIR PLATFORM IN THE
WORLD OF SOCIAL MEDIA IN
GENERAL.
I LOOK FORWARD TO KEEPING OPEN
DIALOGUE.
AS YOU HEARD SUSAN MENTIONED
WHAT IT WAS UP NEARLY 16% ON
MA BECAU A POSITIV
EARNINGS REPORT.
MEANTIME ONE OF T@8 TOP
ADVISORS A■8■8NICATING HIS
THOUGHTS ABOUT THE RAMIFIC■■■ M.
CHIEF WSE CORRESP
JOHN ROBERTS BEGINS THERE ON THE
NORTH LAWN.
>> ONE OF THOSE RARE MOMENTS
WHERE HEHEAR THE FIRST
LAW JARED KUSHNER SPEAK
AT LENGTH.
AT THE FORM WHERE HE HAD
PLENTY TO SAY ABOUT THE MUELLER
REPORT AND THE PATH THAT
CONGRESS IS NOW TAKING.
>> ALL THESE PEOPLE THOUGHT
TRUMP WAS GOING TO LOSE.
>> WING AND FOR THE FIRST TIME
ON THE MUELLER REPORT JARED
KUSHNER DOWNPLAYED RUSSIA'S
REPORT TO INFLUENCE THE ELECTION
INSISTING THE REAL DAMAGE WAS
DONE BY THE ENSUING
INVESTIGATION.
>> YOU LOOK AT WHAT RUSSIA DID
WITH FACEBOOK ADS.■8
2 ■82 IT IS A TERRIBLE THING.
I THINK THE INVESTIGATIONS AND
ALL THE SPECULATION THAT HAS
HAPPENED FOR THE LAST TWO YEARS
HAS HAD A MUCH HARSHER IMPACT ON
DEMOCRACY.
>> HE SAID WHEN MUELLER CAME
CALLING HE WAS THE FIRST ONE TO
RAISE HIS HAND.
SPENDING HOURS WITH A SPECIAL
COUNSEL, HOURS MORE IN
CONGRESSIONAL COMMITTEES AND HE
FULLY EMBRACED AT LEAST ONE OF
HIS FINDINGS.
>> THE MUELLER REPORT WAS
CONCLUSIVE ON THE COORDINATION
OR COLLUSION WITH THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN AND EVERYTHING THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAS BEEN SAYING FOR
TWO YEARS HAS BEEN FULLY
AUTHENTICATED.
>> DEMOCRATS WANT TO KNOW A LOT
MORE ABOUT THE OTHER PART OF THE
MUELLER REPORT.
PRESIDENTIAL EFFORTS TO THWART
THE INVESTIGATION.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS DELIBERATING
WHETHER TO ALLOW FORMER
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL DON BEGAN TO
TESTIFY BEFORE THE HOUSE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE ON MAY 21ST.
THE FORMER CHAIRMAN OF THE
COMMITTEE BELIEVES HE WILL
TESTIFY.
>> I EXPECT HIM TO COME BUT I
EXPECT HIM TO INSIST ON HAVING
PEOPLE BEHIND HIM BACK AND
ADVISE THEM AS TO WHEN TO ANSWER
A QUESTION AND ONE A PRIVILEGE
MIGHT BE APPROPRIATE.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE HAS ALREADY
ADVISED ONE FORMER STAFFER TOIG.
CARL KLEIN THE FORMER CHIEF
PERSONNEL SECURITY WAS TOLD NOT
TO SHOW UP FOR HIS SCHEDULED
DEPOSITION TO THE HOUSE
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE TODAY.
COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN ELIJAH
CUMMINGS SAID HE WILL TAKE A
VOTE TO HOLD HIM IN CONTEMPT.
FOLLOWING THE LEAD OF
SENATOR ELIZABETH WARREN,
ANOTHER 2020 DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE IS ALL IN
ON IMPEACHMENT.
KAMALA HARRIS TELLING THE
TOWN HALL THAT CONGRESS IS TO
ACT.
>> I BELIEVE WE NEED TO GET RID
OF THIS PRESIDENT.
THEY ENGAGED IN OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE AND I BELIEVE CONGRESS
SHOULD TAKE THE STEPS TOWARDS
IMPEACHMENT.
>> AT THE SAME TIME AT THE 100
FORUM, PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
OPPONENT FROM 2016 TOOK A MORE
MEASURED APPROACH TO THE IDEA OF
IMPEACHMENT.
>> YOU DON'T PUT IMPEACHMENT ON
THE TABLE AS THE ONLY ITEM ON
THE TABLE AND SAY YOU WILL GET
THERE NO MATTER.
THAT IS WHAT HAPPENED IN 99.
INSTEAD YOU SAY WE ARE GOING TO
PROCEED WITH THE SERIOUSNESS
THAT THOSE DEMANDS.
>> HILLARY CLINTON KNOWS ALL TOO
WELL WHEN CONGRESS BARRELS DOWN
THAT ROAD TO IMPEACHMENT.
AT THEE TIME AS ALWAYS
CONGRESSIONAL INVESTIGATIONS ARE
HEATING UP AS PRESIDENT TRUMP
WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET OUT OF
WASHINGTON FOR A WHILE, JUST
DAYS AFTER HE RETURNS FROM A
TRIP TO JAPAN TO MEET:H THE
NEW EMPEROR.
HE WILL HEAD UP TO THE U.K. TO
MEET WITH THE QUEEN■
THE CHANNEL INTO NORMANDY TO
COMMEMORATE THE 75TH ANNIVERSAR.
>> Bret: WHAT A DECISION.
>> I HAVE A FEELING THEY WILL
FIGHT MOST IF NOT ALL OF THESE
SUBPOENAS.
I THINK THE SUBPOENA FIGHT IS A
GOOD INDICATION OF■8■ WÑ
ÑLETM THE PRESIDENTÑóÑóÑóóÑóÑOMS
DEADLINE TO TURN OVER SIXEARS
TR■S WAIRESIDENT'S Ró■ó■ó■
THE DEPARTMENT TO ISSUE
A■ REPORT ON THE LEGALITY.
THAT CION WIL BE
TO THE TREASURY TILL÷SECRETARY A
DEADLINE F■■■■■■■■
■■■ MEANTIM■■■■■■■S ARE SOUNDINF
N PAMS FOR OLDER■■■■■■■■■■■■■■E
BECOME INSOLVENT AND■■■■■■■■■■■■
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
STEE■■■
SOCIAL SECURIT■■
■IND.
TONIGHT CORRESPONDENT
KEVIN CORKE LOOKS AT WHERE WE
ARE AND WHAT IT MEANS.
>> THE MEDICARE TRUSTEES REPORT
AND THE MEDICARE HOSPITAL
INSURANCE TRUST FUND IS
PROJECTED TO BE DEPLETED BY
2026.
>> THE 2019 STATUS OF HIS
SOCIAL SECURITY AND MEDICARE
PROGRAMS PAINT AN ALARMING
PICTURE OF THE FUTURE OF
AMERICA'S MOST INSABLE
ENTITLEMENT PROGRAMS.
>> WE NEED TO CHANGE THE
TRAJECTORY OF HEALTH CARE COST
GROWTH TO ENSURE THE SOLVENCY OF
MEDICARE AND MEDICAID.
>> THE REPORT SUMMARIZES THAT
CURRENT PROJECTIONS MEDICARE'S
HOSPITAL INSURANCE FUND WILL
ONLY BE ABLE TO AFFOR■L■L■L
OTAL COST IN JUST SEVEN
YEARS.
SOCIAL SECURITY PROGRAM COST ARE
LIKELY■O■Oññ TO EXCEED TOTAL INN
2020 FOR THE FIRST TIME SINCE
WHILE MEDICARE AND SPECIFICALLY
DICARE FOR ALL HAVE BEEN THE
SUBJECT OF A FIERCE POLITICAL
DEBATE AMONG DEMOCRATS THIS
YEAR, EACH, ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIALS TO THE PROGRAM IS ALSO
INCREASINGLY VULNERABLE.
WITH HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES
SECRETARY WRITING IN A
STATEMENT, AND SET UP TRYING TO
EXPAND MEDICARE INTO A UNIVERSAL
ENTITLEMENT THAT EVEN COVERS
WEALTHY AMERICANS
AGE, W■>■>■>UL
MEDICARE'S PROMISED  SENIO■■ ■■
SENIORS.
>> THE AMERICAN PEOPLE WANT AND
WE ARE GOING■ TO DELIVER A
MEDICARE FOR ALL SINGLE-PAYER
SYSTEM.
>> BERNIE SANDERS HEADLINES A
LARGER FIELD OF CONTENDERS WHO
ALL WITH SANDERS SPECIFICALLYR
ADVOCATING A SINGLE-PAYER
SYSTEM.
>> THEY WILL HURT YOUR
SOCIAL SECURITY SO BADLY.
>> ACCORDING TO THE REPORT THE
NEWS IS EQUALLY BLEAK FOR
SOCIAL SECURITY AND FORECAST OF
THE FUNDS COULD BE DEPLETED BY
2035 AND THAT COULD LEAD TO
REDUCTIONS AND PAYOUTS TO
RETIREES AND OTHER BENEFICIARIE
BENEFICIARIES.
>> THE REAL CONCERN THAT
SOCIAL SECURITY OFFICE IS LIKE
THE ONE BEHIND ME IS THAT WITH
SO MANY BABY BOOMERS NEARING
RETIREMENT AGE AND SOON TO BE
DRAWN OUT OF THE SYSTEM, IT IS
PARAMOUNT THAT SOMETHING BE DONE
TO ADDRESS THE SHORTFALL.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS ASKING
CONGRESSAWMAKERS
■METHBOUT IT SOONER RAT■
■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■8■=
OLITICS, FORMER
LY DECLARE HIS CANDID HIS
THURSDAY. F■%■%ú)■■■■■■■■ TOP■■A
!■!AAAATURE FROM THEcccEARLc PLY
ROLLOUT AND IT C
PO JOE LEADS■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ ■ Ã.
CORRESPONDENT PETER DOOCY TELLS
US WHERE THINGS STAND RIGHT NOW.
SPEAK WITH A LONG TIME
POLITICIAN QUOTING IRISH POETS.
>> I CAN'T LET A COMICAL BIKE
WITHOUT QUOTING AN IRISH POET.
>>
JOE BIDEN WILL ANNOUNCE ANOTHER
WHITE HOUSE CAMPAIGN WITH AN
ONLINE VIDEO THURSDAY WITH A
PITTSBURGH RALLY.
THAT ALL IS A CAMPAIGN IN 1988
CUT SHORT BY PLAGIARISM SCANDALS
AND A CAMPAIGN IN 2008 THAT
TO YOU, I AIN'T GOING AWAY.■■■■■
>> NOW THE 76-YEAR-OLD IS SAID
TO BE THE CANDIDATE.
>> THE WATER IS WARM.
>> KAMALA HARRIS IS ALSO
PITCHING EXECUTIVE ACTION ON
GUNS.
>> UPON BEING ELECTED I WILL
GIVE THE UNITED STATES CONGRESS
100 DAYS TO GET THEIR ACT
TOGETHER AND HAVE THE COURAGE TO
PASS REASONABLE GUN SAFETY LAWS
AND IF THEY FAIL TO DO IT THEN I
WILL TAKE EXECUTIVE ACTION.■■
>> WHAT H SINCE■  HE WAS
THE VICE PRESIDENT MONDAYS AFTER
THE BOSTON MARATHON BOMBING HE
CONDEMNED THE CULPRIT.
>> TWO TWISTED KNOCKOFF SHE
BODIES HERE
IN BOSTON.
>> ANOTHER DEMOCRATIC FRONT
RUNNER WITH A DECLARED CANDIDATE
BELIEVES THAT A SURVIVING BOSTON
BOMBER SHOULD BE ABLE TO VOTE IN
JAIL.
>> IT DOESN'T HURT TO OUR
DEMOCRACY.
EVEN FOR TERRIBLE PEOPLE.
>> ONE THING HE HAS GOING FOR
HIM HIS NAME RECOGNITION.
THEY ARTY KNOW HIS STORY.
AMY KLOBUCHAR'S QUITE THERE YET.
>> I HAVE ONE EVERY SINGLE
CONGRESSIONAL DISTRICT IN MY
BACHMANN'S.DING MICHELLE
THAT IS WHEN YOU ARE SUPPOSED TO
CHEER.
>> ONE CHALLENGE SHOULD BE
GENERATIONAL, MORE THAN TWICE
THE AGE OF PETE BUTTIGIEG WHO
JUST UPDATED HIS WEBSITE WITH
POLICY POSITIONS BUT APPROACHED
ACCUSATIONS THAT HE HAS PUSHED A
HATE HOAX BY ATTACKING MIKE
PENCE.
>> I KNOW BAIT WHEN I SEE IT AND
I WILL NOT TAKE IT.
>> HE WILL BRING LESS THAN A
>> HE GAVE ME PERMISSION TO
TOUC⌞■■8■8■8 IS UNWANTED TOUCHIG
SCAN BROKE OBAMA NEVER
PUBLICLY DEFENDED HIM AND NOW AS
HE REPORTEDLY PLANS TO ALLOT A
LONG LIST OF HIGH-PROFILE
ENDORSEMENTS, IT IS NOT CLEAR
OBAMA WILL BE ONE OF THEM.
>> Bret: PETER, THANK YOU.
WE ARE HAPPY TO ANNOUNCE THE
CANDIDATE PETE BUTTIGIEG WILL
APPEAR ON A FOX NEWS TOWN HALL
MEETING NEXT MONTH, THE
SOUTH BEND, INDIANA, MAYOR WILL
JOIN US FROM CLAREMONT
NEW HAMPSHIRE ON SUNDAY MAY 19TH
AT 7:00 P.M.
CHRIS WALLACE WILL MODERATE
THAT.
WE WILL ALSO HOST MINNESOTA AMY
KLOBUCHAR WEDNESDAY MAY 8TH FROM
MILWAUKEE.
THAT AIR6:30 P.M. MODERATE IN
THAT TOWN HALL.
REPUBLICANS AND THE■■■■■■■■■■■■
CHALT TRUMP.■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
MAY BE CONSIDE■ RUN.D HESHOWED H
KRISTIN FISHER SHOWS US TONIGHT
FROM MANCHESTER, NEW HAMPSHIRE,.
>> I JUST THOUGHT THAT APRIL
WOULD BE A BEAUTIFUL TIME TO
VISIT NEW HAMPSHIRE.
>> THE MARYLAND GOVERNOR LARRY
LOGAN PLAYED COY ABOUT HIS
INTENTIONS AT ATTENDING AND MUST
TOP EVENT FOR PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES.
OVER POLITICS AND ASK THE
GOVERNOR MADE CLEAR HE IS
SERIOUSLY CONSIDERING
CHALLENGING PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> I'M NOT INTERESTING TO BRUISE
THE PRESIDENT.
I'M OUT HERE TALKING ABOUT
THINGS THAT ARE IMPORTANT.
I CARE ABOUT THE FUTURE OF MY
PARTY.
>> THE NATIONAL COMMITTEE DOES
NOT CARE FOR ANY REPUBLICANS
TRYING TO TAKE DOWN
PRESIDENT TRUMP INCLUDING FORMER
MASSACHUSETTS GOVERNOR BILL WELD
WILL OFFICIALLY ENTER THE RACE
LAST WEEK.
>> THEY HAVE THE RIGHT TO JUMP
IN AND LOSE.
THEY WILL LOSE HORRIBLY.
THE PRESIDENT HAS 93% APPROVAL
AND HER PARTY.
>> JANUARY THE COMMITTEE PASSED
A RESOLUTION UNDIVIDED SUPPORT
FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP.
EFFECTIVELY MERGING THE PARTY IN
HIS REELECTION TEAM INTO A
SINGLE UNIT.
>> IT GOES WAY BEYOND WHAT THE
DNC DID IN 2016.
THEY HAVE TAKEN STEPS TO TRY TO
STACK THE DECK IN FAVOR OF THE
PRESIDENT.
IT WAS WRONG WITH A DEAD BUT
THIS HAS MUCH WORSE.
>> HCCUSED PRESIDENT TRUMP OF
TRYING TO COMMIT A CRIME,
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE AND HE
SLAMMED OTHER REPUBLICANS FOR
BEING TOO AFRAID TO SPEAK OUT.
HE AGREES.
>> THEY ARE PETRIFIED OF THE
PRESIDENT BECAUSE THEY KNOW HE
CAN CONTROL HIS EMOTIONS AND HIB
VINDICTIVE.
>> HE IS AWARE THAT AFTER TODAY
HE COULD BECOME
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S NEXT TARGET.
HE BELIEVES HE IS UNIQUELY■■■■■D
OF ATTACK.
>> I BATTLED CANCER FOR 18
MONTHS I CAN PROBABLY TAKE HIM.
>> COULD HEAT ATTEND A CENTURY
OF HISTORY.
wwwo■■■/■■//>■■■■■/>>■■■■■oooo■/
SHANNON BREAM TELLS US WHAT WAS
SAID TODAY.
>> IT IS NOT ABOUT A LINE ON A
FORM.
IT IS ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT
EVERYONE IN AMERICA COUNTS.
>> THEREIN LIES THE PROBL THE
NINE JUSTICES MUST END TABLE.
WHAT ARE THE COMMERCE
SECRETARY OVERSTEPPED HIS
AUTHORITY BY ADDING A
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION TO THE 2020
SENTENCE.
CRITICS OF THE MOVE SAY IT WILL
DISCOURAGE PEOPLE FROM
COMPLETING THE FORMSDICTING
IT WILL LEAD TO AN■■ERCOUNT
PRIMARILY MINORITY POPULATION
SEV LIBERAL
LEANING JUSTICES SAID THE
ADMINISTRATION CAN GET THE
INFORMATION IT IS SEEKING FROM
OTHER GOVERNMENT DATABASES.
HIS DECISION "THIS SEEMS LIKE HE
THOUGHT OF SOMETHING, I WANT TO
ADD A CITIZENSHIP QUESTION."
THIS IS A SOLUTION IN SEARCH OF
A PROBLEM WOULD HAVE TO FIND A
PROBLEM THAT FITS WHAT I WANT TO
DO.
A NUMBER OF THE MORE
CONSERVATIVE JUSTICES NOTED THAT
THE CITIZENSHIP QUESTION HAS
BEEN INCLUDED ON VARIOUS CENSUS
FORMS NEARLY UNIFORMLY BETWEEN
1820 IN 1950.
IN A MORE LIMITED WAY SINCE
THEN.
JUSTICE BRETT KAVANAUGH NOTING
GIVES THE COMMERCEETARY ENORMOUN
PUTTING TOGETHER THE CENSUS FORM
AND HE ASKED WHY A COUNTRY TO
MAKE CONGRESS OBJECTS IT HAS NOT
ABOUT THE QUESTION.
WHY DOESN'T CONGRESS.
BUT THE ASKING OF A CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION IN THE SAME WAY THAT
THAT NCANxyOMPELLED TO
PRLIGIOUS INFORMATION.
OPPONENTS TRACED THE ENTIRE
DEBATE TO IMMIGRATION.
THEY CLAIM THE ADMINISTRATION
AND THE SOLE PURPOSE IS ASKING
ABOUT CITIZENSHIP AS TO SILENCE
PEOPLE IN THE U.S. ILLEGALLY.
THE ADMINISTRATION SAYS THE
PRESIDENT'S PRIORITIES ARE BOTH
LEGAL UNFAIR.
>> WE WANT TO KNOW WHO WAS IN
THIS COUNTRY IT IS A NATION WE
HAVE THAT RIGHT.
>> A DECISION IS DUE BY LATE
JUNE AND TIME IS OF THE ESSENCE.
THE CENSUS FORM, WHAT DO THEY
CONTAIN WITH THE ASSISTANCON HEO
PRINTING PRESSMER.
>> Bret: THANK YOU.
UP■s■s■s■R■R■R■R  CLAIMS
BILITY FOR THE EASTER'S$
SUNDAY MASSACRE, HERE'S WHAT
SOME OF OUR AFFILIATES ARE
COVERING TONIGHT.
FOX 25 IN BOSTON WHERE A FLORIDA
JUDGE HAS ORDERED■■■■■ SEX
NOT BE RELEASED PUBLICLY FOR
NOW.
HE ACCEPTED ARGUMENTS BY HIS
ATTORNEY BY RELEASING THE VIDEO
COULD HARM CHANCES FOR A FAIR
TRIAL.
HE SAYS THAT SHOULD NOT BE
HANDED TO THE MEDIA AS A PUBLIC
RECORD UNTIL THE JURY AS HE DID,
A PLEA AGR IS REACHED■■ OR
THE STATE DROPS THE CASE.■■■s■■H
WHITE FROM FOX TWO, THE BIG
STORY THERE TONIGHT, AUTO SAFETY
REGULATORS EXPANDING
INVESTIGATION INTO A FUNCTIONING
AIRBAG CONTROLS TO INCLUDE
12.3 MILLION VEHICLES.
THEY SAY THE BANKS MAY NOT
INFLATE IN A CRASH, AS MANY AS
FIVE DEATHS ARE ALREADY PLANNED
ON THIS PROBLEM.
IT COVERS PARTS INSTALLED IN
TOYOTA, HONDA, KIA, HON DAY,
MITSUBISHI AND CHRYSLER VEHICLES
FROM 2010OUGH 2019 MODEL
YEARS.
THAT IS TONIGHT'S LIVE LOOK
OUTSIDE THE BELTWAY FROM
"SPECIAL REPORT."
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪ ♪
(ALARM BEEPING)
WELCOME TO OUR BUSY WORLD.
WHERE WE ALL WANT MORE ENERGY.
BUT WITH LESS CARBON FOOTPRINT.
THAT'S WHY, AT BP, WE'RE
WORKING TO MAKE ENERGY
THAT'S CLEANER AND BETTER.
WE'RE PRODUCING
CLEANER-BURNING NATURAL GAS.
AND SOLAR AND WIND POWER.
AND WHEREVER YOUR
DAY TAKES YOU...
WE HAVE ADVANCED FUELS
FOR A BETTER COMMUTE.
AND WE'RE DEVELOPING
ULTRA-FAST-CHARGING
TECHOR EVs..
AT BP, WE SEE
POSSIBILITIES EVERYWHERE.
SO WE CAN ALL KEEP ADVANCING.
♪ LiMu Emu & Doug ♪
What do all these people
have in common, Limu?
[ paper rustling ]
Exactly, nothing.
They're completely
different people,
that's why they
need customized
Car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need!
[ gargling ]
[ coins hitting the desk ]
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done
it again, LiMu.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
■%■Q■R■■Z
♪ ♪
ELCOME BACK TO A
GORGEOUS NIGHT HERE AHE
WHITE HOUSE.
ISRAELI PRIME MINISTER
BENJAMIN NETANYAHU SAYS HE WANTS
TO NAME A NEW SETTLEMENT IN THE
GOLAN HEIGHTS AFTER
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> ALL ISRAELIS WERE DEEPLY
MOVED WHEN PRESIDENT TRUMP MADE
A DECISION TO RECOGNIZE ISRAEL'S
SOVEREIGNTY OVER THE
GOLAN HEIGHTS.
THEY WERE AFTER THE PASSOVER
HOLIDAY I INTEND TO BRING TO THE
GOVERNMENT TO A RESOLUTION
CALLING FOR A NEW COMMUNITY ON
THE■;
PRESIDENT DO TRUMP.
>> Bret: THE HAS BEEN
ANNT ON TWITTER.OUSE REACTION
WE ARE GEW INFORMATIONTONIGHT AN
BEYOND THE EASTER SUNDAY■■■■■■■
COOR BLAST AND SRI LANKA
THE THREAT IS OVER.S AND W
WE A GETTING A LOOK AT
ONE OF THE PERPETRATORS.
HERE IS BENJAMIN HALL.
>> EASTER SUNDAY IN SRI LANKA, A
SUICIDE BOMBER LOOKS CALMLY
TOWARDS SAINT SEBASTIAN'S
CATHOLIC CHURCH IN THE HEART OF
THE CAPITAL RIGHT INTOx÷x÷x÷x÷x.
THE RISING DEATH TOLL NOW STANDS
AT 321 WITH 500 WOUNDED.
AMONG THE DEAD, FOUR■■ AMERICAN,
11-YEAR-OLD, 40-YEAR-OLD, DAVID
KOWALSKI AND SIBLINGS.
15 AND 19 YEARS OLD.
THERE REMAINS A HEAVY POLICE
PRESENCE THERE AS THE
PRIME MINISTER WANTS THERE WERE
MORE MILITANTS AND MORE BOMBS
OUT THERE
GOVERNMENT CLAIMS THE■■■■■■■■■■R
LAST MONTH'S■■■ SHOOTING AT THE
>> SIX■■■■■■■ 3SW ZEALAND■■.A■
■■ QUITE
FRHIS ATTACKA■■■■■■■■■■■■■■IS■■T
BELIEVES THAT THERE IS AN
INTERNATIONAL HELP.
>> ISIS IS CLAIMING
RESPONSIBILITY RELEASING A VIDEO
NOW SHOWING THE NOW DECEASED
MASTERMIND.
HE IS SURROUNDED BY OTHER
SUICIDE BOMBERS WHO CARRIED OUT
PLEDEGIANCE TO ISIS
LEADER.% % % % % % % % % % ■ % E
GOVERNMENT HAS LAUNCHED AN
INQUIRY INTO THE INTELLIGENCE
FAILURE AFTER THE PRIME MINISTER
SAID THE ATTACK WOULD HAVE BEEN
PREVENTED WHEN INDIA HANDED OVER
SPECIFIC INTELLIGENCE TEN DAYS
AGO.
>> IF HE DID RECEIVE HELP FROM
MY ASSIST IT WOULD MARK THE
BEGINNING OF A NEW ERA FOR THE
TERROR GROUP, A CLEAR REMINDER
THEY HAVE TE A■■■■
THREAT.
>> Bret: T.
UP NEXT TO ANOTHER LEGAL PROBL1■
V■V■
FOR ACTOR JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
FIRST BEYOND OUR BORDERS
TONIGHT.
THE MAN IN CHARGE OF THE
RESTORATION OF FIRE AT
NOTRE DAME CATHEDRAL SAID HE HAS
HIRED PROFESSIONAL MOUNTAIN
CLIMBERS TO INSTALL TEMPORARY
TARPS OVER THE BUILDING TO
OFFSET POTENTIAL RAIN DAMAGE
WITH SHOWERS SAID TO HAVE THE
FRENCH CAPITAL THIS WEEK THE
ARCHITECT SAID HE H
THE INSTALLATION OF PROTECTED
COVERS.
ñññ■■OLICE
SAYS IT HAS ARRESTED A WOMAN
UNDER THE TERRORISM ACT WITH THE
SLANG OF THE JOURNALIST.
THE 57-YEAR-OLD FEMALE SUSPECT
WAS ARRESTED TUESDAY, THE ARMY
SPLINTERED GROUP EARLIER
COMMITTED ONE OF ITS VOLUNTEERS
KILLED HER.
SHE WAS FATALLY SHOT WHILE
REPORTING ON RIOTING.
BURMA SUPREME COURT HAS REJECTED
THE FINAL APPEAR OF TWO
JOURNALISTS COME UP HELD A SEVEN
YEAR PRISON SENTENCE IS FOR
REPORTING ON THE MILITARY'S
BRUTAL CRACKDOWN.
THE REPORTERS WERE ARRESTED IN
DECEMBER 2017 AND SENTENCED LAST
SEPTEMBER AFTER BEING ACCUSED OF
ILLEGALLY POSSESSING OFFICIAL
TOISIO Ix.
ADVOCATE THE WJUSTE OF THE OT■8S
BEYOND OUR BORDERS TONIGHT.
BE RIGHT BACK.
♪ ♪
■■■■xxxx■■■■■■■■■
Let's be honest.
It's kind of unfair that
safe drivers have to
pay as much for insurance...
As not safe drivers!
AH!
That was a stunt driver.
That's why Esurance has
this DriveSense® app.
The safer you drive,
the more you save.
Don't worry, I'm not
using my phone
and talking to a
camera while driving...
I'm being
towed.
By the way,
I'm actually
a safe driver.
I'm just pretending to
be a not safe driver.
Cool.
Bye Dennis Quaid!
When insurance is affordable,
it's surprisingly painless.
♪
The right gear...
matters.
Introducing the all-new
2019 Ford Ranger,
It's the right gear.
With a Terrain Management
System for... this.
A bash plate for... that.ç■=
xlectronic Locking Rear
Differential for...
Yeah... this.
Heading to the supermarket?■à
Get any truck.
Heading out here?
Get the Ford Ranger.
(Danny)
Let me get this straight.
The only adventure gear
After a long day of hard work...
...you have to do more work?
(VO)
Automatically sort your expenses
and save over 40 hours a month.
(Danny)
Every day you're nearly fried
to a crisp, professionally!
(VO)
You earned it, we're here to
make sure you get it.
QUICKBOOKS. BACKING YOU.
?=■p
I don't keep track of regrets.
I never count the wrinkles.
And I don't add up the years.
But what I do count on...
is staying happy and healthy.
So, I add protein,
vitamins and minerals to my die.
Delicious BOOST®
High Protein Nutritional Drink
has 20 grams of protein,
along with 26 essential
vitamins and minerals
your body needs.
All with guaranteed great taste.
The upside-
I'm just getting started.
BOOST® High Protein.
Be Up For Life™.
Look for savings on BOOST®
in your Sunday paper.
■
♪ ♪
>> Bret: A LIVE LOOK AT THE
WHITE HOUSE LAWN.
ALEX JONES THE CONTROVERSIAL
HOST, TRUMP SUPPORTER OUT THERE
WITH ABEL LONG AND THAT IS WHAT
YOU HEARD EARLIER.
SOME PEOPLE OUT THERE AS WELL
SAME AS SUPPORT PRESIDENT TRUMP
BUT THEY DON'T SUPPORT WIDER.
HE IS MEETING WITH THE CEO OF
JACK DORSEY HERE AT THE
WHITE HOUSE TODAY.
YOU C BULLHORN AND
THE■■■■ B
IN THE MEANTIME A NEW LEGAL
CHALLENGE FROM THE ACTOR JUSSIE
SMOLLETT TONIGHT.
TWO OF THE MEN INVOLVED IN A
FAKE HATE CRIME ATTACKER NOW
THROWING PUN
HIS  HAS DETAIOM THISER-CHANGIN.
>> GOOD EVENING.
ONE WAY OR THE OTHER WE MIGHT
SAY JUSSIE SMOLLETT AND A■@■@■@R
LEFT COURT ROOM, HE IS F
LAWSUIT FROM THE CITY OF CHICAGO
AND T MIGHT BE CALLED A WITNESS
IN THE FEDERAL LAWSUIT THAT WAS
FILED TODAY.
THE ACTOR WAS NOT NAMED AS A
DEFENDANT.
THEY SAY THE ATTACK WAS A HOAX
CONCEIVED AND DIRECTED BY JUSSIE
SMOLLETT RIGHT OUT OF THE USE OF
A NOOSE, BLEACH AND IT SHOUTS
THAT THIS IS MAKECA GREAT
AGAIN COUNTRY.
THEY CLAIM AFTER CHARGES WERE
DROPPED AGAINST JUSSIE SMOLLETT
THEY DID THE ROUNDS ON NEWS
PROGRAMS AND PODCASTS.
LAWYERS SPUR OF THE BROTHERS HE
REPEATEDLY MADE FALSE
REPREHENSIBLE AND DAMAGING
STATEMENTS, THEY CLAIM THE
REPUTATION AND PERSONAL TRAINING
BUSINESS WERE DAMAGED.
THEY ALSO SUFFERED EMOTIONAL
DISTRESS.
TODAY GLORIA SMITH SAID THE TWO
WANNABE ACTORS FAULTY DIRECTION
OF JUSSIE SMOLLETT AND HOW THEY
WANT TO CLEAR THEIR NAMES.
>> THEY WERE ASKED TO DO
SOMETHING BY A FRIEND THAT THEY
TRUSTED HIM AT THE END OF THE
DAY AT THE FRONT BETRAYED THEIR
TRUST.
>> PART OF HER STATEMENT, "THE
SO-CALLED LAWS WOULD BUY THE
BROTHERS IS MORE OF THEIR LAWYER
DRIVEN NONSENSE AND A DESPERATE
ATTEMPT FOR THEM TO STAY
RELEVANT AND FOR THEIR PROFIT
HE SAYS THE SUITE WILL BE THROWN
OUT BECAUSE IT LACKS LEGA
FOOTING AND THE.
MIKE TOBIN AND
CHICAGO.
THANK YOU.
IN THE MEANTIME M TRYING
TO SHOW THE U.S. IT IS GETTING
MORE SERIOUS ABOUT STOPPING
CENTRAL AMERICAN MIGRANTS FRO
REACHIOUTHERN B
THE U.S.
JONATHAN HUNT LOOKS AT A MAJOR
MOVE THAT TOOK PLACE ON MONDAY.
>> MIGRANTS BOUGHT BACK WITH
STICKS AGAINST WHAT APPEARED TO
BE A CONCERTED EFFORT BY MEXICAN
AUTHORITIES TO SEND A SIGNAL
ACCOMMODATING TO THE THOUSANDS
FROM CENTRAL AMERICA AND
HEADING TO THE U.S. BORDER.
OPERATION WITH■■■■■ OFFIC■■>
G TO REPORTERS ON
SUGGESTING A GROUP OFDREDS
OF MIGRANTS TO TAKE A BREAK IN
THE■■DE ASS FROM■é■ THE
APPROXIMATELY 3,000 STRONG
CARAVAN MOVED ON.
AS THE GROUP RESTED THE MEXICAN
AUTHORITIES MOVED IN.
LARGE NUMBERS OF OFFICERS
GRABBING MEN, WOMEN AND CHILDREN
AND THEM AWAY TO WAITI
BUSES.■■p THAN 350 WERE PICKED N
TOTAL ACCORDING TO MEXICO'S
NATIONAL MIGRATION INSTITUTE
WHICH BL■h THE VIOLENCE ON A
SMALL GROUP OF AGGRESSIVE
MIGRANTS.
JOURNALISTS TRAVELING WITH A
CARAE ALSO REPORTEDLY
MIGRANTSETTING A FAR L
HOSPITABLE WHILE COMPANY MEXICAN
TOWNS THEY TRAVEL THROUGH AND
WAS THE CASE SEVERAL MONTHS AGO.
>> THIS WILL RELY ON MEXICAN
AUTHORITIES TO TAKE A STRONGER
ACTION FRANKLY AGAINST PEOPLE
WHO ARE EXPLOITING MIGRANTS.
>> BORDER PROTECTION OFFICIALS
SHARE THIS VIDEO WITH FOX NEWS
TODAY WHICH THEY SAY WAS SHOT ON
THE ARIZONA MEXICO BORDER ON
SATURDAY AND SHOWS HEAVILY ARMED
SMUGGLERS ESCORTING A GUATEMALAN
WOMAN AND BOY INTO THE U.S.
CBP SAYS IT IS CONCERNED TO SEAT
THOSE SORT OF WEAPONS NOW BEING
USED BY HUMAN SMUGGLERS RIGHT ON
THE BORDER.
>> THE WOMAN AND HER SON WERE
QUICKLY DETAINED BY CBP AGENTS.
THEY MEXICO.
>> Bret: THANK YOU.
JOE BIDEN PUSHES BACK HIS ENTRY
INTO THE 2020 RACE BY A DAY ON
PRESIDENT TRUMP MAY BE GETTING
ANOTHER REPUBLICAN CHALLENGER.
WE WILL TALK ABOUT IT ALL ON THE
2020 ELECTION AFTER THE PANEL
JOINS ME AFTER THE BREAK.
♪ ♪
(Dad) I think it's here.
(Mom VO) Especially at this age.
(Big sister) Where are we going?
(Mom VO) It's a big, beautiful
world out there.
(Little sister) Woah...
(Big sister) Wow. See that?
(Mom VO) Sometimes you just need
a little help seeing it.
(VO) Presenting the all-new
three-row Subaru Ascent.
Love is now bigger than ever.
Sir, you're a broker.
What do you charge for
online equity trades?
Uh, I'll look into it.
(Phone rings)
Lisa Jones!
Lisa: (On phone) Hey Carl,
what are you charging me
for online equity trades?
(Nervous chuckle)
Lisa:
And do I get my fees back
if I'm not happy?
Like a Satisfaction Guarantee?
Ugh. Schwab!
Lisa:
Oh right, I'm calling Schwab.
Thanks, Carl!
Wait, Lisa! Lisa...
Are you getting low costs
backed by
a satisfaction guarantee?
If not, talk to Schwab.
A modern approach to wealth
management.
If not, talk to Schwab.
MY TIME IS THIN,
BUT SO IS MY LAWN.
NOW THERE'S SCOTTS THICK'R
LAWN 3-IN-1 SOLUTION.
■■ñ■ñWITH A SOIL IMPROVER!
SEED!
AND FERTILIZER TO
NOW YARD TIME IS OUR TIM
ATHIS IS A SCOTTS YARD.
nt
There goes our first big order.
♪
44, 45, 46...
How many of these
did they order?
Ooh, that's hot.
♪
You know, we could sell these.
Nah.
♪
We don't bake.
Opportunity.
What we deliver by delivering.
They're America's
biopharmaceutical researchers.
Pursuing life-changing cures
in a country that fosters
innovation
Here, they find breakthroughs...
by arming a patient's own
Like a wT-cells...t cancer
Because it's not just about
the next breakthrough...
It's all the ones after that.
♪ ♪
I BELIEVE CONQUERORS SHOULD TAKE
THE STEPS TOWARDS IMPEACHMENT.
>> OF THE PROCEEDINGS ARE UP TO
THE HOUSE.
>> HE IS MADE IT PRETTY CLEAR
THAT HE DESERVES IMPEACHMENT.
>> EVERY PERSON IN THE SENATE
AND THE HOUSE, THEY SHOULD TAKE
THAT VOTE AND LIVE WITH IT FOR
THE REST OF THEIR LIVES.
>> I WANATION.
WE WILL SEETH■■■■;■■;■■;■■■■■■■0
CANDIDATES AS YOU LOOK AT A LIST
OF EVER-GROWING WITH PEOPLE
GETTING INTO THE RACE.
IT IS A LOT EASIER IT SEEMS FOR
THEM TO SAY GO AHEAD AND IMPEACH
PRESUMP THAN IT IS FOR
DEMOCRATS TONCLUSION.
THE LOGISTICAL HURDLES TO MIKE
AHEAD, YOU LOOK AT THE POLLS
TODAY AS JOE BIDEN
IS IN THE LEAD AND YOU SEE
BERNIE SANDERS AND SECOND, PETE
BUTTIGIEG IS THERE WITH 8% IN A
SHORT TIME AND THEN IF YOU LOOK
AT IOWA, THE FIRST JOB JOE BIDEN
IS ALSO LEADING THERE.
THE MARGIN IS A LITTLE BIT
SMALLER.
THE SOUTH BEND, INDIANA, MAYOR
IS IN THIRD.
WITH THAT LET'S BRING IN OUR
PANEL.
CHARLES HURT OPINION EDITOR FOR
THE WASHINGTON
"THE WASHINGTON POST."
TECHNICAL BIRD, SENIOR EDITOR AT
THE NATIONAL REVIEW.
WE'VE HAD THIS FOR JOE BIDEN, HE
WAS GOING TO GO WEDNESDAY AND
NOW IT IS THURSDAY AND WE DON'T
HAVE A LOT OF DETAILS ON ONE OF
LOOKS LIKE BUT HE'S CLEARLY
STILL LEADING IN SOME OF THESEP.
>> I THINK IS WELL-POSITIONED.
I DON'T USUALLY GIVE A LOT
ADVICE TO DEMOCRATS BUT IF I
WERE HIM I WOULD ANNOUNCE AND
IMMEDIATELY TAKE DEAD AIM AT
BERNIE SANDERS AND SAY THIS IS A
TWO-PERSON RACE AND I'M GROWING
UP.
I'M A LIBERAL BUT I'M NOT A
SOCIALIST ON THE PARTY WILL GO
DOWN IN FLAMES.
IT WILL MAKE EVERYBODY ELSE LOOK
SMALL.
HE IS BASICALLY THE ONLY GUY IN
THE POSITION WHO CAN DO THAT AND
I THINK THAT ONE OF THE THINGS
WE SEE IS THAT A LOT OF THE
DEMOCRATIC PRIMARY PEOPLE THINK
THAT BASICALLY DEMOCRATIC
TWITTER IS THE ACTUAL DEMOCRATIC
ELECTORATE AND IT'S NOT.
HE IS ONE OF THE ONLY PEOPLE WAS
POSITIONED TO ACTUALLY REACH OUT
TO A TRADITIONAL DEMOCRATIC
VOTER.
>> Bret: YOU DO WONDER ABOUT
THE LAUNCH OR DECISION TO LAUNCH
AND WHAT TRANSPIRED THERE.
ALL WE ARE TOLD IS THAT
SOMETHING WILL HAPPEN ON
THURSDAY, A VIDEO LAUNCH AND
THEN A MONDAY EVENT IN
PITTSBURGH.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENS
BETWEEN THURSDAY AND MONDAY BUT
IT'S INTERESTING.
>> ORIGINALLY IT WAS SUPPOSED TO
BE WEDNESDAY AS YOU KNOW AND ONE
OF THE REASONS THEY DELAYED IT,
CHARLOTTESVILLE.
A LOT OF PEOPLE THOUGHT IT MIGHT
BE A GOOD PLACE FOR THE FORMER
VICE PRESIDENT TO ANNOUNCE BUT
THEN THERE WAS SOME KICKBACK
PEOPLE FELT IT WAS DISRESPECTFUL
AND THEY FELT THEY SHOULD DO IT.
THERE IS A "TIME" MAGAZINE PIECE
WHERE THEY HAVE PEOPLE WHO ARE
ALREADY LEAKING WITHIN THE
CAMPAIGN SAYING IT IS VERY
DISORGANIZED FOR A LAUNCH AND
THAT IS A PROBLEM THAT HE WILL
HAVE TO GET ON TRACK.
THE DEMOCRATS ARE NOT WORRIED.
HE IS TO LEADING IN EVERY POLL.
>> Bret: A LOT OF THAT HAS TO
DO WITH NAME RECOGNITION AND
THAT HE WAS A VICE PRESIDENT AND
YOU WONDER HOW JOE BIDEN IS
GOING TO COMPETE WITH A PRETTY
ENERGETIC AND OBVIOUSLY LUMINOUS
CANDIDATE SPREAD ON THE
DEMOCRATIC SIDE.
>> THE PROBLEM FOR JOE BIDEN THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY AND AS A
GENERAL ELECTION CANDIDATE IS
THE FACT THAT HE HAS BEEN A
ROUND WASHINGTON FOR 45 YEARS.
HE HAS BEEN PART OF A PROBLEM
FOR A FOR A LONG TIME AND SO HE
HAS --
HE WILL STRUGGLE TO COME UP WITH
WHATEVER NEW MESSAGE IT IS THAT
HE HAS.
NOW IT WILL CHANGE EVERYTHING
AND OF COURSE WHEN I LOOK AT THE
FIELD I CAN'T THINK OF A SINGLE
PERSON WAS ACTUALLY RUN FOR
PRESIDENT AS MANY TIMES AS HE
HAS OVER THE P■■■ HAS BEEN IN W.
ALL OF THATy AS HE POINTED OUT,
THE NAME RECOGNITION IS VERY
GOOD AND IT HELPS THEM VERY MUCH
HE IS IN A POSITION TO FACEyFFTy
NSyyyyyyyyyyy■
RNIE. DIFFERENCE BETWEENyyyyy■HO
OF THEM, BUT THE PROBLEM STILL
REMAINS THAT HE HAS BEEN AROUND
HERE FOR A VERY LONG TIME.
>> DOESN'T SEEM LIKE HE IS
SETTLED ON A NICKNAME YET.
>> Bret: HE HAD 1%ND HE
HAD SLEEPY JOE, WE DON'T KNOW
WHERE HE WILL END UP.
VOTING RIGHTS FOR PRISONERS CAME
UP LAST NIGHT IN THE TOWN HALL
AND IT SEEMED TO BE A
SEPARATION.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> SHOULD PEOPLE CONVICTED OF
SEXUAL ASSAULT, THE
BOSTON MARATHON BOMBER, SHOULD
THEY BE ABLE TO VOTE?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
EVEN IF THEY ARE IN JAIL THEY
ARE PAYING THEIR PRICE TO
SOCIETY BUT THAT SHOULD NOT TAKE
AWAY THEIR INHERENT AMERICAN
RIGHT TO PARTICIPATE IN OUR
DEMOCRACY.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD HAVE THAT
CONVERSATION.
>> Bret: IS THIS AN ISSUE?
>> IT IS A "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE"
SKIT.
HE GAVE THE EXACT RIGHT ANSWER
AND BERNIE SANDERS AND HIS
POSITION I FIND UTTERLY
BAFFLING.
LOOK, WHEN YOU GO TO THIS THING
CALLED PRISON YOU HAVE LOTS OF
RIGHTS THAT ARE CURTAILED, THE
FREEDOM OF ASSEMBLY AND SPEECH
AND ALL SORTS OF THINGS.
ONE OF THEM THE OTHERS HAPPENS
TO BE FREEDOM TO VOTE.
IT IS ANOTHER THING ENTIRELY
WHEN YOU PAY BACK YOUR DEBT TO
SOCIETY ABOUT VOTING RIGHTS.
THE IDEA THAT BERNIE SANDERS HAS
BURNING FREE CANDY, IS REALLY
ISREORST BE ABLE
TO VOTE, TEST BIZARRE TO ME.
>> Bret: WE TALK ABOUT
MEDICARE FOR ALL AND THE GREEN
IT,■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■ SEEMS LIKE T
PRISONERS VOTING, ELECTORAL
COLLEGE IS ON THE OUTSKIRTS.
>> DEFINITELY.
IN DARK CORNERS IF YOU WILL
DEMOCRATS LIKE MYSELF FOR
SAYING, WHY ARE THEY EVEN MAKING
THIS AN ISSUE?
MAYOR PETE GOT IT RIGHT.
WHEN SOMEBODY COMMITS A CRIME
THEY LOSE THEIR RIGHT AS A FREE
INDIVIDUAL AND NOW WHEN THEY GET
OUT OF PRESENT AND IF THEY GET
THOSE RIGHTS RESTORED THAT IS
ABLE OTHER CONVERSATION.
THIS IS THE CAN OF WORMS THAT
DEMOCRATS DON'T NEED TO OPEN
BECAUSE WE HAVE SO MANY OTHER
AREAS.
THE ONLY GOOD THING IS THAT THIS
IS ONE AREA WHERE THEY ALL DID
NOT AGREE ON THIS ISSUE.
>> Bret: VIEW OF WILLIAM WELD
ON THE REPUBLICAN SIDE THROWING
HIS NAME IN THE HAT, AN UPHILL
BATTLE AND POTENTIAL OF THE
MARYLAND GOVERNOR.
TAKE A LISTEN TO LARRY HOGAN.
>> IT GOES WAY BEYOND WHAT THE
DNC DID IN 2016.
HAVE TAKEN WAY MORE STEPS TO
STACK THE DECK IN FAVOR OF THE
PRESIDENT.
IT WAS WRONG WITH A DEAD BUT
THIS IS MUCH WORSE.
>> THEY CHANGED THE RULES AND TO
INSIST 100% ROYALTY TO THE
LEADER, DIDN'T SOUND MUCH OF THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY THAT I GREW UP
IN.
>> THEY HAVE THE RIGHT TO JUMP
IN AND LOSE.
THEY WILL LOSE HORRIBLY.
>> Bret: YOU DON'T COAT TO
POLITICS IN NEW HAMPSHIRE UNLESS
YOU ARE IT.
>> THAT IS RIGHT.
BY THE WAY I THINK IT IS A GREAT
THING AND IF ANYBODY WANTS TO
GET AN ANSWER OF THE POT IT IS
GREAT BUT THE BOTTOM ONE REMAINS
THAT HE IS ONE OF THE MORE
POPULAR REPUBLICANS AMONG
REPUBLICANS IN RECENT TIMES AND
HE WILL BE THE NOMINEE.
WITH BERNIE SANDERS, I'M CALLING
IT THE 50 STATE STRATEGY TO MAKE
SURE THAT EVEN MASSACHUSETTS
VOTES FOR REPUBLICANS.
WITH CRAZY IDEAS LIKE LETTING
THE BOSTON MARATHON BOMBER'S
GOVERNMENT, A GUY LIKE
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS IN A GOOD
POSITION TO WOULD NOT
REELECTION.
>> Bret: ALEX JONES AGREES
WITH YOU BEHIND■■ THE G■■■■H
HIS MICROPHONE.■■NEXT UP, GRIM R
MEDICARE AND SOCIAL SECURITY.
♪ ♪
Every day,
visionaries are creating
the future.
♪♪
So, every day,
The United States
Postal Service makes
more e-commerce
deliveries to homes
than anyone else
in the c
♪♪
Because the future only
happens with people
who really know how
to deliver it.
Because the future only
happens with people
Incomparable design
makes it beautiful.
State of the art technology
makes it brilliant.
The visionary Lexus NX.
Lease the 2019 NX 300 for
$359 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
Feel the clarity of
non-drowsy Claritin
and relief from
Symptoms caused
by over
200 indoor
Like those
from buddy.
Because st
animals
are clearly no substitute
for real ones.
Feel the clarity.
And Live Claritin clear.
Travel and dining
just go together.
Now KAYAK and OpenTable
let you earn travel rewards
every time you dine.
With just one reservation
on OpenTable,
you can start saving money
on hotels with KAYAK.
Get started at
KAYAK.com/diningrewards.
Don't tell your mother.
Dad, it's fine.
We have ALLSTATE.
AND WITH CLAIMRATEGUARD
THEY WON'T RAISE YOUR RATES
JUST BECAUSE OF A CLAIM.
That's why you're my favorite...
I KNOW.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
Your paycheck. Your family
depends on it.
But if something happened
to you... (woosh)
You need life insurance.
And chances are
SelectQuote can get
it for you for under $1
a day.
SelectQuote found
Alec, 3800,000 policy
for under $23 a month.
SelectQuote found
Kenisha, 37, a
$750,000 policy
for under $23 a month.
SelectQuote's secret? They
impartially shop a select
group of highly rated
companies like these
for your best rates.
Give your family the
security it needs at a
price you can afford.
♪ ♪■■■■■■■>>>÷÷■■r■
>> HEALTH CARE SPENDING IN
AMERICA IS ON AN UNSUSTAINABLE
PATH.
THE MEDICARE TRUSTEES REPORTED
THAT THE MEDICARE HOSPITAL
INSURANCE TRUST FUND IS
PROJECTED TO BE DEPLETED BY
2026.
>> YOU TAKE SOCIAL SECURITY, 25%
OF THE FEDERAL BUDGET THAT'S
GROWING FASTER THAN THE GDP AND
YOU ADD AN MEDICARE AND MEDICAID
AND YOU ARE UP■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■S
NUMB■■■■ FROM THE AIRPORT AS YOU
HEARD MEDICARE SEVEN YEARS FROM
NOW DEPLETED IN THE HOSPITAL
INSURANCE POND.
IT WILL ONLY BE ABLE TO COVER
89% OF THE COST FOR HOSPITAL
STAYS AND RELATED SERVICES THAT
WILL GO DOWN TO 77%.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS SOMETHING HAS
TO■■E■■■■■■■■A■■■ THESE
PROGRAMS IF WE ARE GOING TO DO
THAT.
WE ARE BACK WITH A PANEL.
>> THIS IS A SLOW-GROWING
CATASTROPHE AND NOT SOMETHING WE
HAVEN'T KNOWN FOR A LONG TIME.
OBVIOUSLY PEOPLE LIKE PAUL RYAN
HAVE BEEN TALKING ABOUT IT FOR A
LONG TIME.
PRESIDENT TRUMP RAN INTO
THOUSAND 16 VALLEY NOT TO TOUCH
THESE PROGRAMS.
OBVIOUSLY
THAT WAS A SMART MOVE BACK TEN
BUT THE FACT REMAINS THAT THEY S
AND SOMETHING HAS TO BE DONE
ABOUT IT.
THE ONE GOOD THING I THINK THAT
HAS HAPPENED IS THAT IT WILL BE
A LOT EASIER TO FIX THESE
PROGRAMS WITH A VERY GOOD
ECKE THE ONE WE HAVE■
RIGHT NOW.
IF WE WERE FACING THIS
CATASTROPHE AND HAD A BAD
ECONOMY.
>> Bret: IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
ANYONE IS TAKING THIS BATON?
>> THEY KNEW ABOUT THIS AT LEAST
A YEAR AGO.
YOU HAVE BABY BOOMERS WILL UNDER
THE SYSTEM, YOU PEOPLE WITH A
DOUBLE WHAMMY RIGHT NOW BECAUSE
YOU HAVE INDIVIDUALS LIKE MY MOM
RELY LARGELY ON THEIR
SOCIAL SECURITY TO LIVE.
HOW ON EARTH ARE THEY GOING TO
MAKE UP ANY KIND OF A GAP
MEDICARE IF THEY CAN'T AFFORD
ANY SECONDARY INSURANCED
WHAT THEY ARE ALREADY PAYING.
THIS IS SOM WITH THE■;■■yyyyyyyD
REPUBLICANkkk ONLY CAN WORK
TOGETHER BHA TO.
>> Bret: THE DIFFERENCE IS
PRETTY STARK.
THE WHITE HOUSE REACTION IS THAT
THIS REPORT IS GRAND BUT
MEDICARE FOR ALL IS NOT THE
ANSWER.
>> THEY ARE RIGHT.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS
BASICALLY IGNORED THE PROBLEM
WITH ENTITLEMENTS WHILE THE
DEMOCRATS ARE PROPOSING THINGS
TO MAKE THEM MUCH WORSE.
THE SIMPLE FACT IS THAT WE LIVE
IN AN ECONOMY FOR
SOCIAL SECURITY WAS CREATED,
OVER A DOZEN WORKERS FOR EVERY
RETIREE AND MOST PEOPLE DIED AT
61 AND THEY DIDN'T GET BENEFITS
TILL THEY WERE 65.
WE WERE HAVING A MASSIVE HEALTH
TRANSFER FROM YOUNG PEOPLE TO
ALL PEOPLE AND IT IS NOT
SUSTAINABLE AND IT HAS TO BE
RIPPED UP FROM THE GROUND AND
PEOPLE WHO ARE RECIPIENTS NOWHE
BUT FIX IT FOR THE COMING
GENERATION.
THAT IS NOWHEE HORIZON
FOR THE DEMOCRATS ARE PROPOSING
AND THE REPUBLICANS ARE IGNORING
IT.
>> Bret: MEDICARE PAROLE SEEMS
TO BE A LITMUS TEST FOR A LOT OF
DEMOCRATS
>> UNFORTUNATELY THE IDEA OF
MEDICARE FOR ALL OR PART OF THE
PROBLEMS WE'RE FACING FACING IS
THE TYPICAL GOVERNMENT ANSWER,
MORE CENTRALIZED GOVERNANCE FROM
WASHINGTON AND THAT IS THE WHOLE
PROBLEM OF THE FIRST PLACE.
MAKING MEDICARE, EXPANDI■■■■■■■■
WILL BREAK IT.
>> Bret: THANK YOU.
THE PRESIDENT TWEETED, "THE
STOCK MARKET HIT AN ALL-TIME
HIGH AND THEY ARE TALKING
IMPEACHMENT?
WILL I EVER BE GIVEN CREDIT■■■■E
POLICE OFFICER CONFRONTS A
SITUATION.
♪ ♪
where with migraine.
"I am here."
And I aim to say that more.
Aimovig...
a preventive treatment for
migraine in adults...
reduces the number of monthly
migraine days.
For some, that number can be cut
in half or more.
The most common side effects
are pain,
redness or swelling at the
injection site and constipation.
Aim to be there more.
Talk to your doctor
about Aimovig.
♪ LiMu Emu & Doug ♪
■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Mmm, exactly!
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay
for what you need.
Nice! But uh, what's
up with your partner?
Oh! We just spend all
day telling everyone
how we customize
car insurance
because no two
people are alike, so...
LiMu gets a little
confused when he sees
another bird that
looks exactly like him.
Ya... He'll figure it out.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
Who's idea was this?
♪
♪ ♪é■■■>> Bret: LOVELY
WHE.TONIGHT,OF■y@y■y@y■y■yND, IR
ONE LUCKY SKUNK.
>> I BET YOU THIS WILL GO VIRAL.
>> NOT IN MY
@y@yHEY AREDOINç■y■■■y@y@y
SOMETHING■■■■D.@y
OND, IN CASE DID NOT@8@8@8@8@8@8
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU FOR INVITING US INTO
YOUR HONIGHT, THAT IS IT
FOR THESPECIAL REPORT."
FAIR, BALANCED, AND STILL■ ■