THE S&P 500 IS ON PACE FOR A
RECORD CLOSE, THE FIRST OF 2019.
FOR THOSE KEEPING TRACK IT WOULD
BE THE 81ST RECORD CúOR THE
STOCK MARKET UNDER
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> Bill: REMARKABLE.
>> Katie: THERE IS A BOOMING
STOCK MARKET OUT THERE.
THAT'S IT FOR US.
WE'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW MORNING.
"OUTNUMBERED" STARTS NOW
>> Katie: FOX NEWS ALERT
, IN A SURPRISE DEFAMATION SUIT,
TO GO CHICAGO BROTHERS CAUGHT UP
IN AN ALLEGED HOAX CRIME
ARE ASSUMING THE LAWYERS HAVEESR
JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
THE BROTHERS SAY THEIR NAMES
HAVE BEEN DRAGGED THROUGH THE
MUD OVER A LIE THAT THEY SAY WAS
DIRECTED BY SMOLLETT HIMSELF.
THIS IS "OUTNUMBERED" AND I'M
MELISSA FRANCIS.
HERE TODAY, COHOST OF
"FOX & FRIENDS" FIRST, JILLIAN
MELE.
TOWN HALL EDITOR AND FOX NEWS
CONTRIBUTOR, KATIE HAVE LUNCH.
SYNDICATED RADIO HOST AND
FOX NEWS CONTRg■@■@■@
AND JOINING UN THETODAY FOR THE,
CHARLIE KIRK.
THE FOUNDER AND CEO OF TURNING
POINT USA.
SO GLAD TO GET YOU OUT HERE!
>> Charlie: PLEASED TO BE
HERE, THANK YOU.
>> Melissa: DO YOU FEEL READY?
>> Charlie: I HOPE SO!
[LAUGHTER]
THE TWO BROTHERS FILING AIT.
DEFAMATIONINST
SMOLLETT'S HA)■)
ATTORNEYS, THE■Q BROTHERS WERE
INITIALLY ARRESTED AS SUSPECTS
IN THE ALLEGED ATTACK IN JANUARY
BUT WERE LATER RELEASED.
THEY ARE CLAIMING THA
JUSSIE SMOLLETT PAID THEM "A SUM
OF MONEY" TO STAGE AN ATTACK TO
BENEFIT HIMSELF.
THEY ADD THA THE A DIRECTED
EVERY ASPECT OF THE INCIDENT.
SMOLLETT MAINTAINS THE ATTACK
WAS NOT STAGED.
HERE'S AN ATTORNEY FOR THE
BROTHERS READING THEIR STATEMEN
STATEMENT.
>> THESE LIES ARE DESTROYING OUR
CHARACTER AND OUR REPUTATION IN
OUR PERSONAL AND PROFESSIONAL
LIVES.
THOSE WHO KNOW US PERSONALLY
KNOW THAT WE DON'T HAVE HATE FOR
ANYONE THAT IS NOT WHO WE ARE.
WE WILL NO LONGER SIT BACK AND
ALLOW THESE LIES TO CONTINUE.
>> Melissa: MIKE TOBIN'S LIVE
IN CHICAGO WITH THE LATEST.
MIKE?
>> IT'S IMPORTANT THAT THIS
LAWSUIT DOES NOT NAME
JUSSIE SMOLLETT AS A DEFENDANT,
RATHER, HE NAMES HIS LEGAL TEAM.
THEY SAY THAT AFTER ALL THE
CHARGES WERE DROPPED AGAINST THE
ACTOR, ATTORNEYS MARK GARY GOSE
AND TINA STARTED
DOING THE ROUNDS ON NEWS
PROGRAMS AND BLAMED THE ATTACK
OF THE BROTHERS.
THEY CLAIMED THAT THE STATEMENTS
DAMAGED THE REPETITION OF THE
BROTHERS CAR THEIR BUSINESS, AND
CONSUMMATE THEM EMOTIONAL
DISTRESS.
THEY'RE ASKING FOR DAMAGES AND
LEGAL COSTS.
LAWYERS FOR THE BROTHERS SAY
THEY WANT TO CLEAR THE NAME OF
TWO GUYS WHO WERE JUST TRYING TO
MAKE IT AS ACTORS AND DID WHAT
SUCCESSFUL ACTORS TOLD THEM TO
DO.
THEY SAY THEY WANT TO CLEAR
INTERPRETATION OF THE CITY IN
THE LAWSUIT DOES SAY THAT
>> Sandra: DIRECTED THE OLD
THING
>> THEY WERE ASKED TO DO SOME
BIG DRIVER AND THEY TRUSTED.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, THAT
FRIEND BETRAYED THEIR TRUST.
>> THE LAWSUIT SAYS THAT THEY
CLAIMED ON THE "UNREASONABLE
DOUBT" PODCAST THAT THE YOUNGER
BROTHER BRIEFLY ENGAGED IN
HOMOSEXUAL ENCOUNTER WITH
JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
THAT STORY FLOATED BY THE
JUSSIE SMOLLETT LEGAL TEAM FOR
BY THE BROTHERS WOULD HAVE
ATTACKED SMOLLETT IF IT WAS NOT
AT HIS DIRECTION.
ACCORDING TO A SOURCE FROM THE
SMOLLETT TEAM, ONE BROTHER WAS
WORRIED THAT THE OTHER ONE WAS
GAY AND DIRECTED HIM TO BE THAT
THE ACTOR TO PROVE HE WASN'T
GAY.
THE LAWSUIT SAYS THAT
HOMOSEXUALITY■÷■÷■÷■>■>■÷z÷ NOTF
IN NIGERIAN CULTURE.
>> Melissa: WOW.
THANK YOU FOR THAT.
CHARLIE?
THAT WAS QUITE A NEW REVELATION
FOR PEOPLE THAT WEREN'T
FOLLOWING IT ON THE SITES THAT
PUT OUT THINGS THAT ARE NOT
REPORTED ELSEWHERE.
>> Charlie: I'M FROM CHICAGO
AND IT'S A TOTAL DISGRACE.
I KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHING WRONG
WITH THE STORY ASSUMES THEY
HEARD THAT NEGATIVE 2 DEGREES
WEATHER, HE ALLEGED SOMEBODY
SAID, "THIS IS MAGA COUNTRY."
I'VE NEVER HEARD ANYONE IN
COOK COUNTY USE THAT LANGUAGE
WHATSOEVER.
THERE NEEDS TO BE JUSTICE SERVED
HERE.
IT'S HORRIBLE THAT THOSE FELONY
COUNTS WERE DISMISSED.
THERE'S AN ABUNDANCE OF PEOPLE,
BOTH DEMOCRAT AND REPUBLICAN,
AND CHICAGO.
IT SEEMS LIKE THERE WAS A
CELEBRITY DOUBLE STANDARD HERE.
THAT HE GOT TREATED DIFFERENTLY.
>> Melissa: IT'S AN
INTERESTING APPROACH THROUGH THE
LAWYERS AND NOT THE ACTOR
HIMSELF, FOR DEFAMATION.
PUTTING IT ON THEM, THAT THE
BROTHERS' CHARACTER HAS BEEN
DRAGGED THROUGH THE MUD.
OBVIOUSLY SOMEONE HERE IS LYING.
MAYBE THIS IS A WAY TO GET IT IN
COURT TO IDENTIFY WHO IS TELLING
THE TRUTH AND HE WAS LYING.
>> Leslie: IT SHOULD HAVE
BEEN.
DID AGREE?
[LAUGHTER]
OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS A GOOD START TO A WEEK
THEN.
WHEN YOU HAVE SOMEONE STANDING
THERE SAYING, "WE ARE BEING
DEFAMED BECAUSE WE TOOK MONEY
FROM AN ACTOR TO PRETEND TO BEAT
HIM UP, TO MAKE HIM LOOK BETTER,
AND TO MAKE THIS LOOK LIKE AN
ANTI--GAY AND EVEN ANTIBLACK
CRIME," I'M SORRY, YOU MESSED UP
YOUR CHARACTER IF YOU ARE
ALLEGING THIS IS TRUE.
I'M GLAD IT WILL GO TO COURT
BECAUSE THIS IS TERRIBLE.
THINK ABOUT THE RESOURCES AND,
IN ADDITION TO THAT, HOW MANY
VICTIMS OUT THERE OF RACISM AND
HOW MANY VICTIMS OF HOMOPHOBIA
IN THE LGBTQ COMMUNITY THERE
ARE -- I LIVED IN CHICAGO FOUR
YEARS AND THIS IS TERRIBLE,
ESPECIALLY IN A CITY THAT HAS A
LOT OF TENSION ALONG THE LINES
OF RACE.
>> Jillian: IF I COULD BE
BETTER TO AGREE, I GUESS, AT THE
END OF THE DAY THEY ARE ADULTS.
THEY ARE THE ONES WHO SAID,
"YES, WE WILL DO THIS FOR YOU TO
GET PAID."
AT THE END OF THE DAY, THEY ARE
THE ONES YOU SEE ON THE
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO PURCHASING
THE THINGS USED IN THIS ALLEGED
HOAX.
SO I HAVE A HARD TIME BELIEVING
THEY ARE VICTIMS IN THIS CASE.
>> Katie: THE NEED TO BE HELD
RESPONSIBLE, MAYBE NOT LEGALLY,
BUT PARTICIPATING IN CARRYING
OUT A FAKE HATE CRIME AND THEN
BLAMING WHITE PEOPLE AND
TRUMP SUPPORTERS FOR THAT HATE
CRIME.
THAT'S THE FIRST THING.
THAT BEING SAID, THE FACT THAT
JUSSIE SMOLLETT IS GETTING AWAY
WITH ALL THIS, HIS ATTORNEY WENT
ON "THE TODAY SHOW" AND ACCUSE
THE BROTHERS OF MAYBE WEARING
WHITE FACE AND THAT SO HE SAID
THERE WERE WHITE MEN WHO
ATTACKED HIM WHEN HE WAS TALKING
TO POLICE.
THE THINGS THEY'VE SAID IN HIS
DEFENSE DEFINITELY NOT ONLY
DEFAMED THE BROTHERS, THEY ARE
SAYING THEY STILL CARRIED IT
OUT, EVEN THOUGH THEY DON'T LIKE
HE SAID THEY WERE WHITE.
BUT THE POLITICAL APPLICATIONS
HAVE BEEN DROPPED WHEN IT COMES
TO THE DISCUSSION.
THEY SMEARED AN ENTIRE GROUP OF
AMERICANS AND IT COULD HAVE
CAUSED A LOT MORE DAMAGE IN
TERMS OF THE CULTURE AND
DISCOURSE IN THIS COUNTRY AS A
RESULT OF WHAT THEY DID.
>> Melissa: KNEW DETAILS FROM
INARY CONCALL
WITH DEMOCRATIC■MITTEE CHAIR,
SPEAKER PELOSI URGING FELLOW
DEMOCRATS TO FOCUS ON
INVESTIGATIONS RATHER THAN
IMPEACHMENT IN THE WAKE OF THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL REPORT ON
RUSSIAN INTERFERENCE IN TH■?■■■■
ELECTION.
SPEAKER PELOSI REPORTEDLY
TELLING A
■@■@■@■@■@■yUT DEMOCRAR
REPUBLICANS, IT'S SAVING
WE DON'T HAVE TO GO TO ARTICLES
OF IMPEACHMENT TO GET THE
FACTS."
THEY TELL FOX NEWS THAT
MAXINE WATERS SPOKE UP SAYING
SHE STILL SUPPORTS IMPEACHMENT
BUT WON'T SEEK TO INFLUENCE
ANYONE ELSE ON EDGE.
THE DEMOCRATIC 2020 CONTENDERS
LIKE SENATOR KAMALA HARRIS SEE
NO NEED FOR CAUTION, THOUGH.
WATCH.
>> I BELIEVED CONGRESS SHOULD
TAKE THE STEPS TOWARD
IMPEACHMENT.
BUT I'M ALSO A REALIST.
REPUBLICANS HOLD A MAJORITY.
I HAVE NOT SEEN ANY EVIDENCE TO
SUGGEST THEY WILL BE ON THE
FACTS INSTEAD OF ON PARTISAN
ADHERENCE TO BEING PROTECTIVE OF
THIS PRESIDENT.
AND THAT IS WHAT CONCERNS ME AND
WHAT WILL BE THE EVENTUAL
OUTCOME.
SO WE HAVE TO BE REALISTIC ABOUT
WHAT MIGHT BE THE END RESULT,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN THE
PROCESS SHOULD NOT TAKE HOLD.
>> Melissa: REPUBLICAN MIKE
TURNER SITS ON THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE SAYS
THERE IS PLENTY OF WORK THAT
CONGRESS NEEDS TO DO INSTEAD OF
FOCUSING ON INVESTIGATIONS, AND
HE FELT SPEAKER PELOSI FORGIVING
ENERGY TO A MOVEMENT TO
INVESTIGATE THE PRESIDENT.
>> I THINK THERE'S A LOT OF
DISSENSION IN THE PARTY.
AT THE SAME TIME, SHE IS GIVING
TREMENDOUS ENCOURAGEMENT TO THIS
INVESTIGATION AD NAUSEAM.
THEY SHOULD BE WORKING ON ISSUES
SUCH AS RUSSIA AND CHINA,
NORTH KOREA AND IRAN.
BUT SHE HAS ENCOURAGED
ADAM SCHIFF AND HIS MINIONS TO
CONTINUE THEIR PURSUIT OF
DONALD TRUMP AS IF HE'S THE MOST
SNAGGED A
THREAT TO OUR SECURITY INSTEAD
OF OUR FOES.
IT'S CIRCUMVENTING ROOM WERE
GOING TO BE DONE.
>> Melissa: REPORTING OF THE
WHITE HOUSE BELIEVES THERE IS NO
CHANCE THAT PROCEEDINGS WILL
BEGIN, AND EVEN IF IT DID, IT
WOULD BE A GIFT FOR THE
PRESIDENT.
ONE ADMINISTRATION OFFICIAL
TELLING THE PUBLICATION, "THE
WHITE HOUSE IS SO UNCONCERNED
THAT IT DOESN'T CURRENTLY HAVE A
STRATEGY IN PLACE FOR RESPONDIN/
TO IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS."
>> Charlie: DO YOU BELIEVE
THERE
IS NO PLAN BECAUSE THEY DON'T
THINK
IT'S GOING TO HAPPEN?
DO YOU THINK IT'S SMART?
>> Charlie: I BELIEVE THERE IS
SOME PLAN.
IF THE DEMOCRATS REALLY WANT TO
GO FORWARD WITH THESE ARTICLES
OF IMPEACHMENT -- AND LET'S JUST
SAY IN A HYPOTHETICAL WORLD THAT
IT PASSES.
IT WON'T GO TO THE CENTER.
EVERYONE KNOWS THERE'S HAVE ONLY
BEEN TO PRESIDENTS IMPEACHMENT
ONLY A FEW REMOVED.
ANOTHER LETTER I WORD --
INDEPENDENCE.
UNEMPLOYMENT GOING DOWN, WHICH
IS GOING UP, PIECE HAPPENING
ACROSS THE WORLD.
THEY WANT TO SEE THAT PRESIDENT
IN PHP ARE PEOPLE IN THE MIDDLE
WANT TO SEE UNITY, BIPARTISAN
REFORM, AND IF THE DEMOCRATS USE
THEIR ENERGY ON THAT, THEY WILL
LOSE INDEPENDENTS IN 2020.
>> Melissa: THERE IS SOMEONE
FOCUS ON IMPEACHMENT AND WANTS
IT, AND THAT IS TOM STEYER, WHO
TOOK OUT AN AD.
SAYING, " ALL HERE, TEN
DETAILED ACTS OF OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE."
THE ROBERT MUELLER REPORT LAYS
OUT IMPEACHMENT FOR THE
PRESIDENT."
IT GOES ON TO SAY, "CONGRESS, DO
YOUR JOB.
I'M TOM STEYER."
BUT THAT MESSAGE OUT.
OBVIOUSLY VERY INFLUENTIAL IN
THE PARTY.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> Leslie: I INTERVIEWED TOM
STEYER AND ASKED HIM POINT BLAN
BLANK, BECAUSE TO KAMALA HARRIS'
POINT, THERE ARE REALITIES.
IF IT PASSES THE HOUSE, YOU HAVE
A DIVISION AMONG THE MOST
CENTRIST
LIKE --
HE OF THE REPUBLICAN MAJORITY IN
THE SENATE AND WE HAVE HISTORY O
LOOK TO.
WHAT HAPPENS THERE REPUBLICANS
BUILD PRESIDENT DOMINIC■■■■■
CLINTON
WHAT DOMINIC WAS IMPEACHED?
NEWT GINGRICH --
WHAT HE SAID IS, AND SOME PEOPLE
IN CONGRESS FEEL THIS WAY, MAYBE
ON THE FENCE AS TO WHETHER THEY
WILL BE ON AOC'S SIDE OR
PELOSI'S SIDE OF HIS ARGUMENT
WHICH IS THAT PROGRESS HAS A
RESPONSIBLE LEAD TO THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE, TO CONSTITUTION, TO DO
THE INVESTIGATION.
EVEN IF IT WON'T PASS IN THE
SENATE, BRING THE ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENT BECAUSE OF THEIR
POSITION.
NOT JUST THEIR POSITION, THEIR
CONGRESSIONAL RESPONSIBILITY TO
HAVE OVERSIGHT OVER THE
EXECUTIVE BRANCH.
SPECIFICALLY THE PRESIDENT.
AND HE LOOKED TO TWO ISSUES --
OBSTRUCTION AND WITNESS
TAMPERING.
>> Katie: I THINK IT'S AMAZING
THAT WE ARE CALLING NANCY PELOSI
A MODERATE DEMOCRAT NOW.
SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN AN EXTREMIST.
WE JUST HAVE MORE EXTREMISTS IN
THE PARTY.
>> Leslie: SHE IS PRETTY
MODERATE.
>> Katie: WE'VE GONE FROM
BOB MUELLER AS THE END ALL BE
ALL, WE TRUST WHAT HE'S GOING TO
SAY, WE WILL PROTECT HIM,
BLODGETT
WE
WANTED TO INTRODUCE LEGISLATION
TO PROTECT THEM.
MULTIPLE TIMES THEY WOULDN'T
VOTE ON IT.
AND HERE WE ARE, WITHOUT ANY
KIND OF COLLUSION AND DEMOCRATS
WANT TO FOCUS ON AND OBSTRUCTION
KIND OF YOU
THAT THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL SAYS DOESN'T
PLAY OUT.
MY QUESTION FOR DEMOCRATS -- YOU
SUBPOENAED DOWN AGAIN YESTERDAY
TO COME IN FRONT OF THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE, OR THE
HOUSE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE.
OUT OF THE 30 HOURS OF WHAT HE
TESTIFIED IN FRONT OF MUELLER
ABOUT -- WHICH IS IN THE
REPORT -- WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
FIND BASED ON THE RESOURCES THAT
YOU HAVE AS INVESTIGATORS THAT
BOB MUELLER DIDN'T FIND?
THE ANSWER IS NOTHING.
DEMOCRATS HAVE THE BENEFIT OF
TALKING ABOUT A PATIENT HAS A
TALKING POINT FOR POLITICAL
REASONS, AND ACTUALLY THE
BENEFIT OF INTRODUCING ARTICLES
AND VOTING ON IT BECAUSE THEY
KNOW IT'S NOT GOING TO GO
ANYWHERE.
SO THEY WILL SAY TO THEIR BASE,
"WE VOTED ON IMPEACHMENT, WE
TRIED," AND THE REPUBLICANS
DIDN'T WANT TO HOLD THE
ADMINISTRATION ACCOUNTABLE.
WHEN IT COMES TO HOW WE FEEL BY
THE MUELLER INVESTIGATION, AT
THIS POINT MOST PEOPLE THINK IT
WAS A WITCH HUNT AND HIS
CREDIBILITY WENT DOWN BY THE END
OF THE INVESTIGATION.
PEOPLE JUST WANT TO MOVE ON.
IT'S A DOUBLE-EDGED SWORD BUT I
THINK THE WHITE HOUSE IS MORE
PREPARED THAN THEY ARE LETTING
ON FOR THE INVESTIGATION.
>> Jillian: AND TO YOUR POINT
ABOUT IT BEING A T POINT,
FOR SOMEONE LIKE
KAMALA HARRIS -- WHO KNOWS THAT
HER BASE LOVES THE IMPEACHMENT
TALK -- THEY WILL KEEP TALKING
ABOUT IT.
FOR THE REST OF THE DEMOCRATS, I
FEEL LIKE WE KNOW THAT THERE IS
NO COLLUSION.
SO WE KNEW PEOPLE WOULD HANG
ONTO SOMETHING.
YOU KNEW THEY WOULD STILL
POUNDING THE PAVEMENT ABOUT
SOMETHING.
THAT'S ONE OF THOSE THINGS.
>> Melissa: FOR
KAMALA HARRIS --
>> Jillian: THE DEMOCRATIC
BASE.
>> Melissa: HER AREA OF THE
COUNTRY, WHAT SHE REPRESENTS
NOW, LOVES IMPEACHMENT.
BUT IF SHE'S GOING FOR A BROADER
VOTE AND SHE'S TRYING TO RUN FOR
PRESIDENT, DOES IT STILL MAKES
SENSE FOR HER, CHARLIE?
>> Charlie: IN MANHATTAN AND
MALIBU, IMPEACHMENT IS VERY
POPULAR.
>> Leslie: THERE'S A FEW OTHER
CITIES.
>> Charlie: IN MANHATTAN,
KANSAS, IT'S NOT AS POPULAR.
ALL KIDDING ASIDE, MIDDLE
AMERICA IS STARTING TO SEE THE
REVITALIZATION THAT THEY'VE BEEN
PROMISED FOR DECADES.
WHICH IS GOING UP, MANY
FRACTURING COMING BACK, AND
IMPLEMENT AT RECORD LOW LEVELS.
JUST TODAY, THEY SAID THERE'S
THE LOW EVER BLACK AND HISPANIC
ON EMPLOYMENT.
THE RADICAL LEFT, THEY ARE
DEMANDING REVENGE.
THEY HAVE NOT GOTTEN OVER THE
FACT THAT THEY LOSS IN 2016.
THIS IS THEIR WAY TO TRY AND GET
BACK AT IT.
AT THIS POINT I AGREE --
CONGRESS DOES HAVE AN OVERSIGHT
CAPACITY AND AUTHORITY, 100%.
BUT THEY ALSO DELEGATED THAT TO
ROBERT MUELLER.
WE WERE TOLD FOR TWO,
"GIVE HIM SPACE, GIVE HIM YEARS,
GIVEN $30 MILLION."
NOW THE REPORT COMES OUT AND
THEY HAVE NO COLLUSION.
>> Katie: THEY SAID THEY
WEREN'T INTERESTED IN
give  $30 million."
BECAUSE MUELLER WAS PAID THAT'S
WHAT THEY SAID.
>> Charlie: "LET MUELLER DO
IT."
I'LL I'M CONFUSED, WILL THEY
IMPEACH THEM FOR?
BECAUSE THEY ARE UPSET THAT THEY
LOST?
>> Melissa: TEN ARTICLES OF
OBSTRUCTION.
>> Charlie: IF THEY HAD A CASE
OF OBSTRUCTION, HE WOULD HAVE
REFERRED THAT.
>> Leslie: THE DIFFERENCE HERE
IS THAT SEPARATING CRIMINAL,
WHICH WAS HIS RESPONSE BUILDING,
POLITICAL, WHICH IS ENOUGH AGO,
WHICH IS CONGRESSIONAL
RESPONSIBLY.
>> Charlie: HIGH CRIMES AND
MISDEMEANORS.
IN THE CONSTITUTION IS AS HIGH
CRIMES AND MISDEMEANORS.
SO WHAT CRIME HAVE BEEN CUSTOM
WORK >> Leslie: I KNOW IT SAYS
IN THE CONSTITUTION.
THE INTERPRETATION OF THE
CONSTITUTION -- AND EVEN FORMER
PRESRALD FORD SAID IT --
"IMPEACHMENT IS WHATEVER THE
HOUSE MAJORITY DEEMS IT TO BE AT
THE TIME."
>> Charlie: HIGH CRIMES AND
MISDEMEANORS IS IN THE ACTUAL
LANGUAGE.
NIXON WAS EVER IMPEACHED.
ANDREW JOHNSON WAS FOR A HIGH
CRIME, CLINTON WAS IMPEACHED.
>> Melissa: AT THIS TIME
YESTERDAY WE SHOWED A GRAPHIC
REFERENCING A TREAT FROM
RESIDENT TRIBE REGARDING
MITT ROMNEY'S NOMINATION.
THE GRAPH SHOULD HAVE SAID 2012,
NOT 2016.
WE APOLOGIZE FOR THE ERROR.
COMING UP, THE TOP DEMOCRAT ON
THE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE ACCUSING
THE WHITE HOUSE OF STONEWALLING
AFTER LAWYERS FOR
PRESIDENT TRUMP SUE TO BLOCK
SUBPOENAS FOR HIS PERSONAL
FINANCIAL INFORMATION.
IS HE RIGHT, OR ARE DEMOCRATS
INVESTIGATIONS TOO FAR?
PLUS, 2020 DEMOCRATI
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES CONTINUE
TO PUSH A LIBERAL POLICIES
INCLUDING PLANS TO CANCEL
STUDENT LOAN DEBT AND FINE
EXECUTIVE ORDERS ON GUN CONTROL
AND MORE.
WHETHER VOTERS WILL EMBRACE
THEIR IDEAS, WE WILL DEBATE IT.
NEXT.
>> ON THE FIRST DAY OF MY
ADMINISTRATION, I WILL PUT IN
PLACE A MORATORIUñgñ/w
NO NEW DRILLING, NO NEW MINING
ON ANY FEDERAL LAND.
PERIOD.
♪ ♪
rotein...
To give you
the Protein you need
with less of
the sugar you don't.
(Straining)
I'll take that.
(Cheers)
30 grams of protein
and 1 gram of sugar.
Ensure Max Protein.
In two great flavors.
Don't tell your mother.
Dad, it's fine.
We have ALLSTATE.
AND WITH CLAIMRATEGUARD
THEY WON'T RAISE YOUR RATES
JUST BECAUSE OF A CLAIM.
That's why you're my favorite...
I KNOW.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
♪♪
Be right back.
With moderate
to severe Crohn's disease,
I was there, just not
always where I needed to be.
Is she alright?
I hope so.
So I talked to my doctor
about HUMIRA.
I learned HUMIRA is for people
who still have symptoms
of Crohn's disease
after trying other medications.
And the majority
of people on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom relief
and many achieved remission
a■■■■■ections,■&■d■d■ RAery
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
■g
including lymphoma, have
happened; as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Ñ
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Be there for you, and them.
Ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA,
remission is possible.
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
■■■■g■■■■■■■GGG■G■■■■■■■■O■ç=■=■
What do all these people
have in common, LiMu?
[ guttural grunt ]
Exactly. Nothing!
They're completely
different people.
That's why they
make customized
car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need.
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done it again, LiMu.
[ LiMu grunts ]
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
♪ ♪
>> WE ARE GOING TO ROLLBACK
STUDENT LOAN DEBT FOR ABOUT 95%
OF STUDENTS WHO HAVE IT.
THAT'S PART ONE.
PART TWO IS TO MAKE SURE WE
NEVER GET IN THIS MESS AGAIN ON
THE STUDENT LOAN DEBT, AND THAT
IS TO MAKE COLLEGE UNIVERSALLY
AVAILABLE WITH FREE TUITION AND
FEES.
>> Katie: 2020 DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL HOPEFUL,
SENATOR ELIZABETH WARREN,
ROLLING OUT AMBITIOUS LIBERAL
POLICY PROPOSALS AT A TOWN HALL
LAST NIGHT.
WARREN ADDRESSING THE STUDENT
DEBT CRISIS.
HER PLAN INCLUDES CANCELING
STUDENT LOAN DEBT, ELIMINATING
N AND FEES AT PUBLIC
COLLEGES, AND GREATER SUPPORT
FOR MINORITY AND LOW INCOME
STUDENTS.
HERE IS HOW SHE WOULD PAY FOR
IT -- MAKING SUPER WEALTHY
AMERICANS PAY MORE IN TAXES.
>> I STARTED IN SEVERAL MONTHS
AGO TALKING ABOUT A WEALTH TAX.
AN ULTRA MILLIONAIRE'S TAX.
NOW THAT YOU'VE GOT THAT GREAT
FORTUNE, SPEND JUST A MINUTE TO
REMEMBER HOW YOU GOT IT.
AND WE SAY, "GOOD FOR YOU, THAT
YOU HAVE NO GOTTEN THIS GREAT
FORTUNE.
BUT TWO SENSE -- YOU'VE GOT TO
PAY SOMETHING BACK SO EVERYONE
ELSE GET THE CHANCE."
>> Katie: CRITICS AIRPLANE TO
BE DIFFICULT TO IMPLEMENT AND
WOULD SPUR MORE AGGRESSIVE TAX
AVOIDANCE.
MEANTIME, PRESIDENT KENNEDY AND
FELLOW SENATOR KAMALA HARRIS IN
ANOTHER TOWN HALL SAYING SHE
WILL
USE THE POWER OF THE PEN TO
COUNTER GUN CONTROL OF CONGRESS
IS NOT.
>> I WILL GIVE THEM 100 DAYS TO
GET THEIR ACT TOGETHER AND HAVE
THE COURAGE TO PASS REASONABLE
GUN SAFETY LAWS.
IF THEY FAIL TO DO IT, THEN I
WILL TAKE EXECUTIVE ACTION.
WHAT I WILL DO IS PUT IN HER CAR
MENTOR EVERYONE WHO SELLS MORE
THAN FIVE GUNS A YEAR -- THEY
ARE REQUIRED TO DO BACKGROUND
CHECKS WHEN THEY SELL THOSE
GUNS.
Katie: MELISSA, I■# TO
GO TO FIRST ON THE MONEY ASPECT
OF THE STUDENT LOAN SITUATION.
IT'S COMPLICATED.
WAS YOUR RESPONSE TO
ELIZABETH WARREN'S PROPOSAL?
>> Melissa: HOW TO PAY FOR IT
IS ALWAYS TO TAX THE RICH.
EVERYONE SAYS THAT EVERY TIME.
REMEMBER WHEN THEY TRIED THAT IN
FRANCE AND A WHOLE BUNCH OF
PEOPLE LEFT?
DIDN'T WORK.
THE REAL POINT WAS THEY DIDN'T
TAKE IN NEARLY THE REVENUE THAT
THEY HAD CALCULATED.
BECAUSE A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE TOO
SMART AND THEY LEFT THE COUNTRY.
THEY EVENTUALLY HAD TO REPEAL
IT.
IT DIDN'T WORK OUT.
I WOULD ALSO SAY THAT IF YOU
CONFISCATED THE WEALTH OF THE
TOP 1% AND THREW THEM IN JAIL
AND TOOK AWAY EVERYTHING THEY
EARNED IN A YEAR, IT WOULD BE A
FEW TRILLION DOLLARS AND YOU
COULDN'T PAY FOR ALL OF THESE
PROGRAMS THEY ARE TALKING ABOUT.
MEDICARE FOR ALL, STUDENT LOAN,
ALL OF THOSE THINGS.
THERE ISN'T ENOUGH RICH PEOPLE
TO PAY FOR WHAT THEY WANT TO.
EVEN IF HE TOOK AWAY THEIR
EARNINGS AND THROUGH THEM IN
JAIL.
>> Katie: CHARLIE, YOUR FORTE
IS WORKING WITH YOUNG PEOPLE,
YOUNG MILLENNIALS WERE IN
COLLEGE COME OUT OF COLLEGE.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO SAY ABOUT
HER PROPOSAL?
>> FIRST OF ALL, I DON'T THINK
IT'S VERY FAIR FOR STUDENTS WHO
WORKED THEIR WAY THROUGH COLLEGE
AND HAD MANAGEABLE STUDENT LOAN
DEBT.
THIS CATERS TO STUDENTS THAT HAD
TENS OF THOUSANDS AND HUNDREDS
OF THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS IN
STUDENT LOANS.
I THINK THEY ARE VICTIMS AND A
LOT OF SENSE.
THERE'S ALSO SO MUCH
MISINFORMATION ABOUT THIS,
THOUGH.
EVEN CONGRESSWOMAN MAXINE WATERS
A COUPLE THINGS GO THOUGHT SHE
WOULD DO A GOTCHA QUESTION AT
THE BIG BANKS, ASKING WHAT THEY
WERE DOING ABOUT STUDENT LOANS.
LITTLE DOES SHE KNOW, MOST OF
THEM ARE GIVEN OUT BY THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT.
WE'VE NATIONALIZED OUR STUDENT
LOAN INDUSTRY.
ALSO, TO SENATOR WARREN, WE NEED
TO ASK A QUESTION -- SHOULD WE
HAVE AS MANY PEOPLE GOING TO
FOUR-YEAR COLLEGE THAT WE HAVE
GOING TO COLLEGE RIGHT NOW?
THE ANSWER IS NO.
THE NATIONAL GRADUATION RATE IS
59%.
THAT MEANS 41% OF PEOPLE WHO
ENTER COLLEGE WILL NOT GRADUATE.
WE HAVE TOO MANY PEOPLE GOING TO
FOR YOUR COLLEGE.
IS IT WORTH GETTING INTO DEBT?
THESE ARE QUESTIONS WE SHOULD
ADDRESS BEFORE YOU SAY WE SHOULD
FORGIVE IT.
AND ALSO TAKE MONEY AWAY FROM
PEOPLE HAVE 11 BE QUITE
SUCCESSFUL TO PAY FOR A
COMPLETELY BROKEN SYSTEM.
FINAL POINT, WHY NOT TAX THE
ENDOWMENTS?
SHE IS SO SILENT OF THOSE.
I'LL TELL YOU WHY -- SHE GETS
CONTRIBUTIONS.
SHE WANTS TO WORK WITH THE
BIGGEST ENDOWMENTS OF THE WORLD.
>> Katie: JILLIAN, YOU WERE
NODDING HER HEAD.
>> Jillian: YOU ARE TALKING
ABOUT THE KIDS HE WORKED TO PUT
THEMSELVES THROUGH COLLEGE.
WHAT ABOUT THE PEOPLE WHO HAVE
WORKED THEIR ENTIRE LIVES AND
CAME FROM NOTHING TO BE ABLE TO
MAKE SOMETHING OF THEMSELVES AND
MAKE THEMSELVES PERHAPS
SELF-MADE MILLIONAIRES?
WHY SHOULD THEY HAVE TO PAY FOR
EVERYTHING FROM OTHER PEOPLE?
GOING BACK TO THAT WHOLE 2% TAX
ON FAMILIES WITH $50 MILLION OR
ABOVE, I GET IT, YOU'VE GOT A
LOT OF MONEY, BUT AT THE SAME
TIME IT DOESN'T MEAN YOU GIVE IT
AWAY.
>> Katie: LESLIE, I'M WANTING
THE DEMOCRAT RESPONSE HERE.
SHE'S ARGUING WE HAVE TO STOP
HER FROM HAPPENING AGAIN, WHICH
I AGREE WITH.
BUT AS WE SEE THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT HANDING OUT LOANS
WITHOUT ANY KIND OF RETURN ON
INVESTMENT OR REAL CALCULATION
OF WHAT IS GOING TO MEAN IN
TERMS OF THE CAREER YOU GO INTO,
WE SEE THIS MASSIVE PROBLEM AND
CRISIS WITH STUDENT LOAN DEBT.
AND NOW REGULAR PEOPLE AND
FELLOW MILLENNIALS -- THERE'S
LOTS OF THE LIMOS WHO HAVE
MORTGAGES.
SHOULD WE ALSO BAIL THEM OUT ON
THAT?
WHERE DOES IT END?
>> Leslie: FIRST OF ALL, WE
HAVE TO REMEMBER THAT EVERY
PERSON WE ARE HEARING FROM --
ELIZABETH WARREN AS WELL, IS
CAMPAIGNING TO GET THAT
NOMINATION FOR DEMOCRAT
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
SHE HAS A SEPARATE HERSELF FROM
THE REST.
A LARGE NUMBER OF HER SUPPORTERS
ARE BERNIE SANDERS SUPPORTERS,
WHICH WE HAVE SEEN IN THE POLL
THAT MILLENNIALS LOVE BERNIE.
FOR TWO REASONS.
FREE COLLEGE TUITION HAS
BIPARTISAN SUPPORT.
THE LEFT AND RIGHT, PEOPLE SAY
IT'S A BROKEN SYSTEM THAT NEEDS
TO BE FIXED.
ANOTHER THING, WHEN
BETO O'ROURKE STOOD UP A COUPLE
WEEKS AGO AND GAVE OUT HIS GREAT
TALK, THERE WAS A QUESTION THAT
SAID, "WHAT IS YOUR SPECIFIC
PLAN FOR THAT?"
AND HE COULDN'T ANSWER THAT.
TO HER CREDIT, SHE SAID, "THIS
IS MY SPECIFIC PLAN."
IT'S VERY AMBITIOUS, I DON'T
THINK IT WOULD WORK BECAUSE IT
WOULDN'T BEEN ABLE TO BE
ENFORCED WITH PEOPLE WHO ARE
THAT WEALTHY BECAUSE THEY HAVE
THE ABILITY TO HIRE PEOPLE TO
HAVE THE MONEY.
>> Melissa: WHY DON'T YOU MAKE
THE UNIVERSITY'S PAY FOR IT?
INSTEAD OF THE TAXPAYER BEING
THE ONE TO FOOT THE BILL FOR ALL
THIS DEBT, THE UNIVERSITIES OF
THE ONE THAT ARE GRADUATING
PEOPLE WITH DEGREES THAT ARE, BY
DEFINITION -- BECAUSE THEY ARE
NOT BEING PAID BACK -- NOT WORTH
WHAT PEOPLE PAID FOR THEM.
THEY ARE NOT ABLE TO GET A JOB
AND PAY BACK THE DEBT BECAUSE
THE DEGREE WASN'T WORTH HOW MUCH
OF COLLEGE CHARGED FOR IT.
IN A NORMAL MARKET IT WOULD BE
THE COLLEGE THAT TOOK THE HIT.
THAT GOES BACK TO YOUR IDEA OF
THE ENDOWMENTS.
MAKE THE COLLEGE STOMACH THE
LOSS.
THEY WILL GET THEIR FINANCES IN
ORDER, THEY WILL GET THEIR
PRICES IN LINE.
BUT JUST SLOUGHING EVERYTHING
OFF ON THE TAXPAYER IS THIS
UNNAMED PERSON.
THERE IS NO INCENTIVE THERE, AS
YOU SAID.
>> Melissa: I WANT TO GET A
RESPONSE TO KAMALA HARRIS ON THE
GUN-CONTROL ISSUE.
>> Charlie: FIRST OF ALL, ANY
EXECUTIVE ACTION ON GUNS WOULD
BE QUICKLY APPEALED BY MANY
SECOND AMENDMENT ADVOCATES.
IT GOES TO SHOW THERE ARE SO
MUCH IN FRONT DON'T LIKE
MISINFORMATION WITH FIREARMS,
MORE SO EVEN THE STUDENT LOANS.
MOST OF THE DEATHS ARE HANDGUNS
IN URBAN AREAS WITH GANG-RELATED
VIOLENCE.
I DID NOT HEAR ONES IN HER
CAMPAIGN SPEECH THE LAST COUPLE
WEEKS TALKING ABOUT THE SYSTEMIC
ISSUES, WHITE GANG VIOLENCE IS
HAPPENING.
TWO REASONS -- PUBLIC SCHOOLS IN
FATHERLESS HOUSES.
THEY ARE TAKING LAW-ABIDING
WEAPONS AWAY FROM AMERICANS
THAT'S NOT GOING TO DO ANYTHING
TO SOLVE THE ISSUE.
>> Katie: ALL RIGHT, MOVING
ON.
THIS UP IN COURT WEARING A BIG
CASE WHETH RTE A
QUESTION ABOUT CITIZENSHIP ON
WHY THIS HAS BECOME
CONTROVERSIAL AND WHETHER IT
SHOULD BE.
♪ ♪
NewDay USA helps veteran
homeowners get cash
by using the powerful VA
home loan benefit
we've earned with
our service.
The NewDay VA Cash Out
Loan can help you
get over 50,000 dollars to pay
off  the credit card debt,
put cash in the bank,
and reduce your payments
by over 500 dollars a month.
And since NewDay's
been grantedUUHH■■■
Automatic Authority
by the VA,
they can say yes when
banks say no.
Get the financial security
you've ed deserve.
Call 1-833-844-6706
Whoooo.
Did you know the exact same
hotel room...
...can have many different
prices?
That's why TripAdvisor searches
over 200 booking sites
to find the lowest price on the
hotel you want.
Your perfect hotel room for the
perfect price!
Oh!
♪ Ozempic®! ♪
(announcer)
People with type 2 diabetes
are excited about
the potential
of once-weekly Ozempic®.
In a study with Ozempic®,
a majority of adults
lowered their blood sugar
and reached an A1C
of less than seven
and maintained it.
Oh!
Under seven?
And you may lose weight.
In the same
one-year study,
adults lost on average
up to 12 pounds.
Oh!
Up to 12 pounds?
A two-year study showed
that Ozempic® does not
increase the risk
of major cardiovascular events
like heart attack,
stroke, or death.
Oh!
No increased risk?
♪ Oh, oh, oh, Ozempic®! ♪
Ozempic® should not be the first
medicine for treating diabetes,
or for people with
type 1 diabetes■■
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not share needles or pens. .
Do not take Ozempic® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine Neoplasia
Syndrome type 2,
get a lump or swellingic®
and get min your neck,ight away
severe stomach pain, itching,
rash, or trouble breathing.
Serious side effects
may happen,
including pancreatitis.
Tell your doctor if you have
diabetic retinopathy
or vision changes.
Taking Ozempic® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
48ease the risk
for low blood sugar.
Common side effects are nausea,
vomiting, diarrhea,
stomach pain, and constipation.
Some side effects
can lead to dehydration,
which may worsen
kidney problems.
I discovered the potential
with Ozempic®.
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! Ozempic®! ♪♪
Ask your
healthcare provider today
about once-weekly Ozempic®.
You're headed down the
highway when the guy in
front slams on his
brakes out of nowhere.
You do, too, but not in time.
Hey, no big deal.
You've got a good record
and Liberty Mutual
won't hold a grudge by raising
your rates over one mistake.
You hear that, Karen?
Liberty Mutual
doesn't hold grudges.
How mature of them!
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
♪ ♪
>> Jillian: WELCOME BACK.
A MAJOR TEST FOR THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION BEFORE THE
SUPREME COURT TODAY, WHEN THE
JUDGES HEAR ARGUMENTS OVER
WHETHER THE INITIATION CAN PUT A
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION ON THE 2020
CENSUS.
SUPPORTERS SAY IT WILL HELP
ENFORCE VOTING RIGHTS AND HAS
BEEN DONE ON THE PAST.
CRITICS SAY IT'S A VEILED
ATTEMPT TO DISCRIMINATE AGAINST
NONCITIZENS, DISCOURAGE THEM
FROM PARTICIPATING, AND IT WAS D
RESULT IN UNDERCOUNTING THE
PUBLISHING.
THEY SAY THIS QUESTION IS BASED
ON THE CONSTITUTIONAL PRINCIPLE
THAT WILL IMPACT THE ENTIRE
COUNTRY AND HURT THE
REPRESENTATION OF MINORITIES.
PREFEDERAL COURTS HAVE BLOCKED
THE COMMERCE DEPARTMENT FROM
ADDING THE CITIZENSHIP QUESTION.
COURTS HAVE RULED THAT COMMERCE
SECRETARY WILBUR ROSS VIOLATED
FEDERAL LAW AND THE WAY HE WENT
ABOUT TRYING TO INCLUDE THE
QUESTION ON THE CENSUS.
MELISSA, I WILL GO WITH YOU --
WHAT DO YOU SEE HAS PROS AND
CO
>> Melissa: AKE THE
POLITICS OUT OF IT -- WHICH, YOU
KNOW, IT'S ALWAYS HARD -- IN
THIS CASE I THINK IT REALLY
COUNTS.
HOW DO YOU GET THE BEST PICTURE
OF WHO IS WHERE?
I HONESTLY DON'T KNOW THE ANSWER
TO THAT, BECAUSE YOU WANT THE
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION IN
THEIR
BECAUSE YOU WANT TO KNOW WHERE
THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO ARE TAXPAYF
FUNDING, WHO NEEDS WHAT, WHAT IR
@■X■XHE ELECTORAL COLLEGE.
SO I WANT TO KNOW WHO IS REALLY
RARE.
AT THE SAME TIME, I DON'T WANT
TO DISCOURAGE PEOPLE FROM NOT
RESPONDING TO THE CENSUS BECAUSE
THEY ARE AFRAID AND THEY ARE
HERE ILLEGALLY.
BECAUSE I WANT AN ACCURATE
COUNT.
SO I DON'T KNOW, BETWEEN THOSE
TWO STATES, WHAT THE BEST WAYS
TO GET AN ACCURATE COUNT.
>> Katie: BUT THERE IS NO
DISTINCTION IF YOU ARE HERE
ILLEGALLY OR A CITIZEN ON THE
CENSUS NOW.
SO IT'S NOT DETERMINED.
WE STILL DON'T HAVE AN ACCURATE
COUNT OF THE NUMBER OF ILLEGAL
IMMIGRANTS IN THIS COUNTRY.
THE PROBLEM WITH THIS IS OF THE
CENSUS IS USED TO DELEGATE
CONGRESSIONAL DISTRICTS AND IT'S
RIDICULOUS THAT WE ARE COUNTING
NONCITIZENS OR ILLEGAL ALIENS IN
THE --
>> Jillian: SORRY TO INTERRUPT
YOU, KATIE.
WE HAVE A FOX NEWS ALERT.
>> Melissa: FOX NEWS ALERT, WE
CAN ALL CONFIRM THE
VICE PRESIDENT                FR
VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN IS
GOING TO ANNOUNCE HIS
RESIDENTIAL RUN ON THURSDAY.
WE HAD BEEN HEARING IT WOULD
HAPPEN ON WEDNESDAY IN
CHARLOTTESVILLE, VIRGINIA.
IT HAD BEEN SLATED, WE HAD
THOUGHT, RUMORED FOR OTHER
TIMES, AS WELL.
THIS, HE'S GOING EFFICIENTLY
ANNOUNCE HIS RUN ON THE
THURSDAY.
OH, BY A VIDEO ANNOUNCEMENT IS
WHAT BE HER HEARING.
HE WILL DO IT BY VIDEO.
A LOT OF DETAILS CHANGING WE
COME OUT.
LET ME BRING ITTO THE COUCHm>
■>m>m>
CHARLIE, WHAT DO
THE FACT THAT HE IS GOI
WE ARE HEARING THE LATEST --
THAT HE'S GOING TO DO A VIDEO
MESSAGE?
AND THE DATA HAS CHANGED AGAIN,
BUT NOW IT SEEMS TO BE FIRM.
>> Charlie: AND NOT TOO SURE
ABOUT THE VIDEO ASPECT.
IT'S INTERESTING, YOU THINK YOU
WOULD WANT THE BIGGEST CROWD
POSSIBLE.
MAYBE THEY HAVE TROUBLE BUILDING
THE SAME CAR THAT KAMALA HARRIS
WOULD BUILD.
BY THE WAY, SHE HAD AN AMAZING,
CALIFORNIA.
MAYBE HE DOESN'T WANT THE
QUESTION TO BE THAT HE CAN'T
BUILD A CROWD.
I WILL SAY THIS -- IT WILL GET
VERY NASTY VERY QUICKLY.
HE WILL COME IN WITH A LOT OF
MONEY AND ADDRESSES AND MEDIA
CONNECTIONS.
THEY WILL LOOK AT HIM AS THE
SINGULAR BULL'S-EYE THE SAME WAY
THE CANDIDATES LOOKED AT
JEB BUSH IN 2016.
>> Melissa: WE ARE ALSO
CONFIRMING HE WILL MAKE AN
APPEARANCE ON MONDAY IN PERSON
AS A CANDIDATE IN PITTSBURGH.
VIDEO ON THURSDAY TO MAKE THE
OFFICIAL ANNOUNCEMENT, AND THEN
THE MONDAY AS A CANDIDATE IN
PERSON IN PITTSBURGH.
WHY DO YOU THINK THE C■
HEARD BEFORE OR DO■
WERE FLOATED AND THEY WERE NEXT
AND NOT FIRM?
>> Leslie: I THINK THEY HAD
FIRM PLANTS A DISH TO DO
CHARLOTTESVILLE AND PITTSBURGH
AND PHILLY ON WEDNESDAY,
TOMORROW.
IT WAS SMART FOR THEM.
IT WOULD BE VIEWED AS
DISRESPECTFUL.
MY UNDERSTANDING FROM MY SOURCES
OVER THERE, THEY BASICALLY ARE
SAYING, "LOOK, HE WANTS TO SAY
THAT PEOPLE IN THIS COUNTRY
RETURN OF THE HATE.
TIRED OF THE DIVISION.
I WANT TO UNITE AND BRING US
TOGETHER.
I WANT TO HELP THE FIX AND
REPAIR THE WOUNDS."
NOT A GOOD PLACE TO DO IT.
PENNSYLVANIA, VERY SMART PLACE
FOR THEM TO BE.
NOT ONLY SEE FROM THERE,
PENNSYLVANIA HAS ONE OF THE
THREE STATES THAT HELPED PUT
THEM IN THE WHITE HOUSE ALONG
WITH WISCONSIN AND MICHIGAN AND
A STATE WHERE JOE BIDEN IS VERY
POPULAR, A LOT OF BLUE COLORS
WORKER BLUE-COLLAR
WORKERS NOT VERY HAPPY.
>> Melissa: DID THIS CHANGE IT
SEEM?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Katie: THE ROLLOUT HAS BEEN
CLUMSY.
IT HURTS JOE BIDEN.
YOU LOOK AT THE POLLING,
BERNIE SANDERS HAS GAINED ON THE
MEND IS THAT IF AND WHEN SOME OF
THE EARLY STATES.
IT'S A VERY EARLY, SO THAT CAN
CHANGE.
HOWEVER, I FIND IT INTERESTING
THAT WE KEEP SAYING JOE BIDEN IS
THE GUY WHO'S GOING TO BRING
EVERYONE TOGETHER.
GOING TO UNIFY EVERYBODY.
JOE BIDEN IS THE GUY WHO IS VERY
GOOD AT DIVISION THEN VERY GOOD
AT STOKING THE FLAMES.
VERY CONTROVERSIAL ISSUES ON THE
CAMPAIGN TRAIL.
WAS A 2016 HE SAID REPUBLICANS
WOULD PUT EVERYONE BACK IN
CHAINS WHEN HE WAS SPEAKING --
MITT ROMNEY, 2012?
WHEN HE WAS SPEAKING TO AN
AFRICAN-AMERICAN AUDIENCE.
HE HAS SAID SOME PRETTY VILE
THINGS THAT HE TENDS TO GET AWAY
WITH BECAUSE HE'S NOT
DONALD TRU
>> Jillian: I KIND OF AGREE
WITH WHAT YOU SAID, LESLIE,
ABOUT HOW IT MAY NOT HAVE
BEEN -- AND IS NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN NOW -- THE BEST BET TO DO
IT IN CHARLOTTESVILLE PAID EVER
BUT HE AGREES, IF YOU WERE GOING
TO DO IT SOMEWHERE,
PENNSYLVANIA, SCRANTON,
PHILADELPHIA EVEN.
THAT WOULD'VE BEEN A BETTER MOVE
SO IT FEELS LIKE THEY ARE
PLAYING THE SAFE CARD AND DOING
>> Leslie: CAN IMAGINE THE
POLLS CUSTOMER TO YOUR POINT
ABOUT THE POLL, THERE WAS A
MORNING CONSUL POLE THAT SHOWED
HIM LEADING
BY 30%.
THAT IS OVER SANDERS BY 6%.
TEN DAYS AGO JOE BIDEN WAS
LEADING.
I DON'T THINK THAT JOE BIDEN
LOST HALF OF HIS SUPPORTERS IN
TEN DAYS.
I'M JUST SAYING, I DON'T BELIEVE
ALL THESE POLLS.
>> Katie: THEY'VE NEVER BEEN
WRONG BEFORE!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Leslie: SHOCKING!
>> Jillian: WE WILL CERTAINLY
KEEP AN EYE ON
JOE BIDEN SUCH JUMP INTO THE
PRESIDENTIAL RING AND SOME NEW
POLLING -- THAT WE LOVE -- WITH
SOME VERY INTERESTING NEWS FOR
HIM.
WHAT YOUNG PEOPLE ARE SAYING
ABOUT HIM AND BERNIE SANDERS
WHEN WE
COME BACK.
♪ ♪■■
■■
Le'íat some■=of 5u■
stroke, their first symptom...
IS a stroke.
80 percent of all strokes and
heart disease? Preventable.
And 149 dollars is all it takes
to get screened
and help take control
of your health.
We're Life Line Screening...
and if you're over 50...
call THIS number, to schedule
an appointment...
for FIVE painless screenings
that go beyond
regular check-ups.
We use ultrasound technology to
literally look
INSIDE your arteries...
for plaque which builds up as
you age-
and increases your risk for
stroke
and cardiovascular disease.
And by getting them through this
package, you're saving over 50%.
So call today and consider these
numbers:
for just $149 you'll receive
five screenings
that could reveal what your body
ISN'T telling you.
I'm gonna tell you that was
the best $150
I ever spent in my life.
Life Line Screening. The Power
of Prevention.
Call now to learn more.
Hold my pouch.
Trust us. Us kids are ready to
take things into our own hands.
Don't think so? Hold my pouch.
a heart problem.
■■■
I was told to begin my
Aspirin regimen,
and I just didn't listen.
Until I almost lost my life.
My doctors again ordered
me to take Aspirin,
and I do.
Be  Listen to ■.e■ your docton
Take it seriously.
>> Jillian: A FOX NEWS ALERT,
VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN WILL
MAKE HIS CANDIDACY OFFICIAL ON
THURSDAY, THIS IS NEW
POLLING SHOWS THAT THE YOUNG
DEMOCRATIC VOTERS ARE FEELING
THE BURN FOR BERNIE SANDERS.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO A NEW
NATIONAL POLL LOOKS AT
LIKELY PRIMARY VOTERS BETWEEN
THE AGES OF 18 AND 29.
IT SHOWS THAT
SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS WITH A
LEAD OVER FORMER VICE PRESIDENT
JOE BIDEN WITH FORMER
CONGRESSMAN BETO O'ROURKE
TRAILING IN THIRD PLACE.
THE POLL ALSO FINDS SHARP
CHANGES IN SUPPORT BASED ON
CATEGORIES LIKE GENDER.
YOUNG MEN GIVING SANDERS THE
EDGE OVER BIDEN, BUT SANDERS'
LEAD NARROWS CONSIDERABLY AMONG
YOUNG WOMEN.
I WILL START WITH YOU.
WHY DO YOU THINK THE YOUNGER
GENERATION LOVES BERNIE SANDERS?
>> Leslie: HE STARTED A
REVOLUTION.
IF YOU REMEMBER, WHEN HE RAN
AGAINST HILLARY CLINTON, HE
WASN'T JUST A CANDIDATE.
IT WAS A REVOLUTION.
YOUNG PEOPLE OF THAT.
PROTESTS, TO REVOLT ABOUT
SOMETHING.
IN ADDITION, HE PROMISES FREE
STUFF.
FREE HEALTH CARE, FREE TUITION.
HAVING TROUBLE PAYING THE
STUDENT LOANS?
IF YOU HAVE TO DO A SECOND JOB
OR GET A MINIMUM WAGE JOB, I'M
GOING TO FIGHT FOR $15 AN HOUR."
THEY LIKE THAT.
IT RESONATES WITH THEM.
WHAT ALSO RESONATES IS THAT HE
HAS PORTRAYED HIMSELF AS A
CHAMPION OF THE OPPRESSED AND
THEY TRULY FEEL OPPRESSED.
>> Jillian: BUT THIS MESSAGE
HASN'T WORKED IN THE PAST.
HE TRIED TO COME AND GO TO YOU.
PART OF WHAT I THINK IS GOING
ON -- A LITTLE BIT, ANYWAY -- IS
GETTING THE MESSAGING OUT.
YOU LOOK AT SOMEONE LIKE
ALEXANDRIA OCASIO-CORTEZ, HE
DOES SO MUCH ON SOCIAL MEDIA,
YOU HAVE YOUNG PEOPLE WHO LISTEN
TO OUR MESSAGE.
YOU FEEL THAT SOMEONE LIKE HER
IS HELPING HIM IN THIS MOVEMENT?
>> Charlie: YOU ARE.
I AGREE WITH WHAT HE SAID.
SOME VILLANELLES DO FEEL
OPPRESSED.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
YOU LIVE IN THE GREATEST COUNTRY
IN THE WORLD WITH MORE
OPPORTUNITY THAN EVER BEFORE.
LIFE
EXPECTANCY EXPANDING, WHICH
IS GOING UP, YOUTH AND IMPLEMENT
LOWER THAN WE'VE EVER SEEN.
MORE JOB OPENINGS THAN PEOPLE TO
FILL THOSE JOBS.
WHICH ARE THEY FEEL OPPRESSED
ABOUT?
THAT THERE UBER EATS WAS LATER
THERE WAS A LONG LINE AT
STARBUCKS?
[LAUGHTER]
HE FOCUSES ON TWO THINGS -- HE
PROMISES AN UNATTAINABLE UTOPIA,
AND NUMBER TO BECOME A PLAYS
INTO THIS VICTIMHOOD CULTURE
THAT THE UNIVERSITIES TRAIN
ENTS TO PROGRAMMATICALLY
FOCUS ON.
HEONVINCES THEM THAT EVERYONE
IN THE YOUNGER GENERATION IS
DESERVING OF EVERYTHING FROM
BEFORE THEM.
THE SYSTEM IS RIGGED AGAINST
YOU, THEREFORE ITS ABILITY AND
OUR MONEY THAT YOU DESERVE.
IT'S TENDER STUFF.
>> Katie: HE'S ALSO BLIND T
YOUNG PEOPLE.
WHEN HE PROMISES FREE
HERE IS NO SUCH
THING AS FREE.
SOMEONE WILL PAY FOR IT.
IF YOU DO THE MATH ON HIS
PROPOSALS, WHETHER IT'S FREE
COLLEGE OR FREE MEDICAL CARE,
YOU HAVE TO ACTUALLY TAX
EVERYBODY.
WHICH HE ADMITS.
"ALL OF YOUR TAXES WILL GO UP
BUT THEN YOU WILL HAVE FREE
SERVICES," WHICH ALSO WASN'T
TRUE.
WE SOME REPORTS OF MEDICARE AND
SOCIAL SECURITY GOING INSOLVENT.
THOSE AREN'T WORKING AND HE
CONTINUES TO LIE TO THEM ABOUT
IT.
HE'S A HYPOCRITE.
LAST NIGHT DURING HIS CNN
TOWN HALL HE WAS ASKED ABOUT THE
TERM TAX CUTS AND HE RAILED
AGAINST THEM EVEN THOUGH HE GOT
A TAX CUT AND ISN'T WILLING TO
WRITE A CHECK FOR THE DIFFERENCE
OF THE GOVERNMENT.
>> Jillian: MELISSA, I'M
CURIOUS -- PEOPLE ARE RALLYING
BEHIND HIM AND HIS METHOD RIGHT
NOW.
ULTIMATELY DO THINK THEY VOTE
FOR HIM?
>> Melissa: THAT'S A VERY
INTERESTING QUESTION.
I LIKE THIS POLL, IT'S FROM THE
INSTITUTE OF POLITICS AT THE
KENNEDY SCHOOL AT HARVARD.
THEY WELCOMED ME AS A SPEAKER
AND THEY HAD ME THERE WITH
ANOTHER DEMOCRAT WHO WARNED ME
BEFORE I WENT OUT AND SAID,
"THESE KIDS ARE SO LIBERAL, THEY
SHOCK EVEN DEMOCRATS."
EVERYONE WHO COMES TALK TO THEM,
THEIR FRUIT IS LEFT OF ANYTHING
THAT YOU COULD POSSIBLY IMAGINE
BE READY."
THEY HAD VERY INTERESTING
QUESTIONS BUT IT WOULDN'T
SURPRISE ME AT ALL THAT THEY
WOULD LET WHOEVER THE FARTHEST
LEFT CANDIDATE IS.
I LOVE THE IOP!
GO, GUYS.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Charlie: THE FINAL POINT I
WILL MAKE IS THAT IT'S VERY EASY
TO BE GENEROUS WITH OTHER
PEOPLE'S MONEY.
IT'S EASY TO HAVE --
>> Leslie: BUT HE HAS SAID
HE'S A DEMOCRATIC SOCIALIST.
>> Katie: MAYBE HE SHOULD PAY
WITH HIS MILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
MAYBE HE WILL AN OUT HOUSE TO
MILLENNIUM.
>> Charlie: IF THE GOVERNMENT
IS THE BEST WAY TO RIGHT THE
WRONGS OF THE CAPITALIST SYSTEM,
YOU SHOULDN'T GIVE ANY MONEY TO
CHARITY.
TO GOVERNMENT.
HE SHOULD NOT GIVE CHARITABLE
CONTRIBUTIONS.
JUST GIVE IT TO THE IRS.
>> Katie: HE SHOULDN'T SELL
HIS BOOK ON BARNES & NOBLE OR
AMAZON, EITHER.
SPEED WENT ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT AFTER THE
BREAK.
IN THE MEANTIME, FOX NEWS IS NOW
SET TO HOST ANOTHER BIG
TOWN HALL EVENT.
DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENT CANDIDATE
MARY PETE BUTTIGIEG WILL SIT
DOWN WITH OUR OWN CHRIS WALLACE
IN THE EARLY VOTING STATE OF
NEW HAMPSHIRE.
YOU CAN CATCH IT ON SUNDAY,
MAY 19TH, AT 7:00 P.M. EASTERN.
RIGHT HERE ON    ON FOX NEWS CH.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO WATCH
THAT.
A LEGAL BATTLE IS BREWING
BETWEEN PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
HOUSE OVERSIGHT CHAIRMAN
ELIJAH CUMMINGS OVER THE
PRESIDENT'S PERSONAL FINANCIAL
RECORD.
IS THIS LEGITIMATE OVERSIGHT OR
HAVE DEMOCRATS GONE TOO FAR?
THAT'S.
>> THEY TRY THESE TYPE OF
RIDICULOUS TACTICS IN THE PAST
TO PUSH THINGS LIKE TAX RETURNS.
IT'S ALREADY BEEN LITIGATED IN
THE COURT OF PUBLIC OPINION AND
IN THE ELECTION THE PRESIDENT
WON FAIRLY AND SQUARELY.
HE IS THE PRESIDENT AND NO ONE
CARES ABOUT RIDICULOUS CHARGES
ABOUT TAX RETURNS.
♪ ♪
■ú■■■L]>b■bo#w& &&■■■■■■wnoí>
Is this ride safe?
I assembled it myself last
night.
I think I did an OK job.
Just OK?
What if something bad happens?
We just move to the next town.
Just OK is not OK.
Especially when it comes to your
netw
AT&T is America's eless
network
according to America's biggest
test. Now with 5G Evolution.
The First Step to 5G.
More for your thing. That's our
thing.
♪ ♪
>> Katie: HOUSE OVERSIGHT
CHAIRMAN ELIJAH CUMMINGS
RESPONDING TO THE LAWSUIT FILED
AGAINST HIM BENT TRUMP
AND THE TRUMP ORGANIZATION
YESTERDAY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S LAWYERS MOVING
TO BLOCK SUBPOENAS FOR FINANCIAL
INFORMATION FROM THE PRESIDENT'S
BUSINESSES.
CHAIRMAN CUMMINGS RESPONDING,
"THE PRESIDENT HAS A LONG
HISTORY OF TRYING TO USE
BASELESS LAWSUITS TO ATTACK HIS
ADVERSARIES, BUT THERE IS SIMPLY
NO VALID LEGAL BASIS TO
INTERFERE WITH THIS DULY
AUTHORIZED SUBPOENA FROM
CONGRESS."
THE SUIT ASKED THE FEDERAL COURT
IN WASHINGTON TO KEEP CHAIRMAN
COMING CUMMINGS FROM OBTAINING
RECORDS FROM THE ACCOUNTING FIRM
THE PRESIDENT AND HIS BUSINESSES
USE.
JAY SEKULOW, COUNSEL TO THE
PRESENT, SING THIS IN A
STATEMENT -- "WILL NOT ALLOW
CONGRESSIONAL PRESIDENTIAL
HARASSMENT TO GO UNANSWERED
TO."
CHARLIE?
>> Charlie: WHAT'S HAPPENING
IS THE DEMOCRATS ARE TRYING TO
ASSEMBLE THE GREATEST
TAXPAYER-FUNDED OPPOSITION
RESEARCH FILE ON DONALD TRUMP
THEY POSSIBLY CAN.
THAT'S ALL THIS IS.
THEY WERE DISAPPOINTED BY THE
MUELLER REPORT'S OF THE STAR TO
REPOSITION ALL OF THEIR
STRATEGIES A COUPLE MONTHS AGO
WHEN PEOPLE STARTED TO LEAVE
MILLER'S TEAM, STARTED TO SIGNAL
THEY WOULDN'T HAVE THIS
BOMBSHELL.
I HAVE TO GO BACK TO THIS -- FOR
THE LAST YEAR AND A HALF WE HAVE
HEARD■@■■=>
NANCY PELOSI ESSAY AMAZING
THINGS ABOUT BOB MUELLER.
THAT THIS MUELLER REPORT WITH
THE END OF THE PRESIDENCY,
MUELLER IS COMING.
ANOTHER POINT IS OUT AND THEY
WANT MORE INFORMATION.
THIS GOES TO SHOW THEY ARE MUCH
MORE FOCUSED ON DESTABILIZING
THE PRESIDENCY OF DONALD TRUMP
THAN ACTUALLY DOING WHAT'S BEST
FOR AMERICA.
>> Katie: LESLIE,
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS ELECTED THE
FIRST TIME WITHOUT RELEASING HIS
TAX RETURNS.
DOES IT REALLY MATTER AT THIS
POINT?
FIVE THERE ARE COUPLE THINGS.
TO YOUR POINT, I WOULD DISAGREE.
SINCE HE'S BEEN CAMPAIGNING THEY
HAVE GONE AFTER HIS TAX RETURNS
BEFORE HE EVEN HEARD THE NAME
BOB MUELLER.
THAT IS SOMETHING THAT DEMOCRATS
WANT.
ONE OF THE REASONS THEY WANT IT
IS IF YOU ARE ASKED FOR
SOMETHING VIA A SABINA AND HE
PUSHED BACK, WHAT
IT'S LIKE, "O.J., WHY ARE YOU
RUNNING AWAY IN THE CAR?
HE MUST BE GUILTY AND HIDING
SOMETHING."
I THINK THAT'S WHAT THEY FEEL.
THE MOST COMPREHENSIVE VIEW, IF
YOU'RE GOING TO DO AN
INVESTIGATION AND YOU'RE GOING
TO FOLLOW A MONEY TRAIL, YOU
NEED TO SEE ALL THE MONEY THAT
HAS BEEN REPORTED AND HAS BEEN
RECEIVED.
INCLUDING BISE BUSINESS.
>> Melissa: COME ON, LET'S BE
HONEST.
THEY WANT TO LOOK AT IT TO SEE
WHAT THEY CAN FIND IN THERE TO
HURT HIM IN THE NEXT ELECTION.
IT WAS A RISK TO SAY THAT YOU
WEREN'T GOING TO PUT YOUR TAX
RETURNS BEFORE YOU WERE ELECTED,
BECAUSE THEN, YES, VOTERS COULD
SAY MAYBE HE'S HIDING SOMETHING
WE SHOULD SEE.
HE TOOK THAT RISK, HE DIDN'T PUT
THEM OUT, AND HE WON.
THAT'S THAT.
AND OF THE STORY.
NO ONE HAS A RIGHT TO IT NOW.
THEY DIDN'T HAVE A RIGHT TO IT
BEFORE.
YOU COULD HOLD IT AGAINST
MASSIVE VOTER AND YOU STILL HAVE
THAT OPPORTUNITY TO DO IT.
HE'S NOT RELEASING THEM AGAIN,
SO VOTERS WILL ONCE AGAIN HAVE
THE OPPORTUNITY, IF THEY CHOOSE,
TO HOLD IT AGAINST THEM.
THEY DID LAST TIME, WE WILL SEE.
MAYBE IT'S DIFFERENT NOW.
>> Jillian: JUST BECAUSE
YOU'RE SAYING NO TO RELEASE
SOMETHING, DOESN'T NECESSARILY
MEAN -- I GET WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING, BUT IT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU'RE GUILTY OR THAT THERE IS
SOMETHING TO FIND.
IT JUST MEANS NO.
>> Leslie: EVERY DEMOCRAT AND
REPUBLICAN WHO HAS RUN -- EVEN
IN LOCAL OFFICES -- SHARES THEIR
TAX RETURNS.
>> Melissa: BECAUSE THEY FELT
COMPELLED TO DO IT.
THAT'S WHAT MADE IT SUCH A HUGE
RISK THAT HE DIDN'T DO IT.
THAT'S WHAT MADE IT■dH A RISK.
>> Leslie: BUT WHAT IS THE
MOTIVATION FOR NOT DOING IT?
>> Melissa: BECAUSE HE KNOWS
IT'S A HUGE DOCUMENT.
ANYONE WHO DOES REAL ESTATE IN
NEW YORK, IT'S A HUGE DOCUMENT.
■÷■÷w÷w÷w÷■÷w÷■÷w÷w÷w÷ THROUGH D
FIND SOMETHING.
>> Katie: IT WILL BE USED AS A
POLITICAL WEAPON.
>> Melissa: NOT ILLEGAL
THING.
>> Charlie: SOMETHING THAT'S
NOT TALKED ABOUT ENOUGH -- WHAT
A GIFT TO HIS COMPETITORS, ALL
TH■■■■NS, WHO WANT TO
SEE THE IN-DEPTH FINANCIALS OF
ALL HIS ASSETS.
HE'S TRYING TO PRESERVE A
BUSINESS ENTERPRISE THAT HE HAS
SPENT DECADES AND LOTS OF RISK
PUTTING TOGETHER.
IF HE WANTS THE NEXT GENERATIONS
TO BE ABLE TO HAVE IT.
WHY WOULD HE GIVE HIS FINANCIALS
TO THE HILTONS, THE MARRIOTTS,
TO ALL THE OTHER COMPETITORS
THEY CAN IN-DEPTH LOOK?
HE SHOULDN'T GIVE THOSE
FINANCIALS.
BY THE WAY, I WILL DEFEND THAT
HE HAS A RIGHT TO PROTECT IT.
>> Leslie: HE DIDN'T GET INTO
DEL MIKE VOTED INTO OFFICE TO
PROTECT HOTELS AND WALL STREET.
>> Charlie: BUT HE HAS A RIGHT
TO KEEP THEM PRIVATE.
>> Melissa: VOTERS KNOW THAT.
VOTERS ARE SAYING, "YOU DON'T
PUT IT UP BECAUSE YOU WANT TO
PROTECT YOUR COMPETITIVE
ADVANTAGE."
>> Katie: MORE "OUTNUMBERED"
IN JUST A MOMENT.
♪ ♪
who need cash.
With home values rising
all across the country,
now's the time to use your
valuable VA home loan benefit.
NewDay USA can
help you refinance
and get 54,000
dollars or more
AND lower your payments
by $600 a month.
And since they've been granted
Automatic Authority by the VA,
NewDay can say yes
when banks say no.■■■
So if you're a veteran
homeowner who needs cash,
now's the time to
call NewDay USA.
Go to NewDayUSA.com
or call 1-800-420-9803
Alright, I brought in
Ensure Max Protein...
To give you
the Protein you need
with less of
the sugar you don't.
(Straining)
I'll take that.
(Cheers)
30 grams of protein
and 1 gram of sugar.
Ensure Max Protein.
In two great flavors.
Excuse me a minute...
Hi Dad. No.
Don't try to get up.
Hi, I'm Julie, a
Right at Home caregiver.
And if I'd been caring
for Tom's dad,
I would have noticed
some dizziness that
could lead to balance issues.
That's because I'm trained to
report any changes in behavior,
no matter how small, so Tom
could have peace of mind.
We'll be right there.
We have to go.
Hey, Tom.
You should try Right at Home.
They're great for us.
The Right Care. Right at Home.
>> Katie: THINK YOU TO CHARLIE
KIRK.
ANYTHING COMING UP?
>> Charlie: TRAVELING TO
PENN STATE UNIVERSITY TODAY WITH
DONALD TRUMP JR.
WE WILL HAVE A LOT OF FUN.
>> Katie: DEBATING WHO?
>> Charlie: ANY LEFTIST WHO
WANTS TO STEP UP TO THE
MICROPHONE.
ANOTHER TURNING POINT USA EVENT.