>> Katie: THINK YOU TO CHARLIE
KIRK.
ANYTHING COMING UP?
>> Charlie: TRAVELING TO
PENN STATE UNIVERSITY TODAY WITH
DONALD TRUMP JR.
WE WILL HAVE A LOT OF FUN.
>> Katie: DEBATING WHO?
>> Charlie: ANY LEFTIST WHO
WANTS TO STEP UP TO THE
MICROPHONE.
ANOTHER TURNING POINT USA EVENT.
>> Katie: WILL BE BACK
TOMORROW AT NOON EASTERN.
BUT NOW, MELISSA FRANCIS IS IN
FOR HARRIS.
>> Melissa: FOX NEWS ALERT,
JOE BIDEN IS SET TO ANNOUNCE
ANOTHER RUN FOR THE WSE
ON THURSDAY.
WELCOME TO
"OUTNUMBERED OVERTIME."
I'M MELISSA FRANCIS IN TODAY FOR
HARRIS FAULKNER.
FOX NEWS CAN NOW CONFIRM THAT
JOE BIDEN WILL MAKE HIS
CANDIDACY FOR THE PRESIDENCY
OFFICIAL IN TWO DAYS IN AN
ONLINE VIDEO.
SOURCES FAMILIAR WITH THE
PLANNING SAY THE FORMER
VICE PRESIDENT WILL ALSO MAKE AN
APPEARANCE ON MONDAY INffo■PITT.
ñ■LD WHEREñññññ■■V■■■■■■■■■■■Ñ■■
PAOGRESSIVE IDEAS WERE
FRONT AND CENTER DURING A SERIES
OF 2020 TOWN HALLS LAST NIGHT,
INCLUDING ELIZABETH WARREN
ANNOUNCING Ajjj TO CANCEL
EXIS STUDENT DEBT■jjjj■■■■■jj■jF
CONGRESS DOESN'T ACT IN HER
FIRST 100 DAYS.
AND BERNIE SANDERS DEFENDING HIS
STANCE TO GRANT VOTING RIGHTS TO
CRIMINALS WHILE THEY ARE IN
PRISON, INCLUDING THE BOSTON
MARATHON■■G■
JUST DAYS AFTER THE SIXTH
ANNIVERSARY OF THE ATTACK.
PETER DOOCY HAS MORE ON ALL OF
THIS FROM WASHINGTON.
IT'S HEATING UP, PETER.
>> MELISSA, A VIDEO ANNOUNCEMENT
ON THURSDAY MORNING AND A
PITTSBURGH RALLY ON MONDAYx■x■tD
AT■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■.
IN 1988 HE DROPPED OUT EARLY AND
NEVER MADE IT TO THE PRIMARIES,
AMID A PLAGIARISM SCANDAL.
IN 2008 OUT AFTER IOWA
AND LATER BECAME BARACK OBAMA'S
RUNNING MATE.
IN 2019 HE'S HOPING FOR BETTER
AGAINST A FIELD WHERE THE NUMBER
ONE DECLARED CANDIDATE RIGHT NOW
IS BERNIE SANDERS.
WHO DOES NOT SEEM CONCERNED THAT
PRIMARY OPPONENTS OR MAYBE EVENE
HIS DEFENSE OF THE BOSTON
BOMBER'S RIGHT TO VOTE AGAINST
HIM.
>> MY FOLLOW-UP QUESTION GOES TO
THIS, YOU'D LIKE YOU ARE
OPPOSITION AT AGAINST YOU BY SAN
BOMBER SHOULD DO IT.
NOT AFTER HE PAYS HIS DEBT TO
SOCIETY, BUT WHILE HE'S IN JAIL.
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
>> I THINK I HAVE WRITTEN MANY
30-SECOND OPPOSITION ADS
THROUGHOUT MY LIFE.
>> KAMALA HARRIS LATER SAID
ABOUT DEATH OR INMATES WOULD
ENCUMBER THAT SHE SUPPORTS
HAVING THAT CONVERSATION.
THE CALIFORNIA SENATOR MADE A
BIGGER SPLASH ABOUT EXECUTIVE
ACTION ON GUN CONTROL WITHIN THE
FIRST 100 DAYS OF TAKING OFFICE,
IF SHE DOES, AND CONGRESS
DOESN'T ACT.
>> I WILL REQUIRE THAT FOR ANY
GUN DEALER THAT BREAKS THE LAW,
THE ETF TAKE THEIR LICENSE.
BY THE WAY, ATF -- ALCOHOL,
TOBACCO, AND FIREARMS -- THEY'VE
BEEN DOING A LOT OF E AND T BUT
NOT MUCH OF F.
WE NEED TO FIX THAT.
>> ELIZABETH WARREN TO TRY TO
SEW A DIFFERENT POLICY.
CANCELING STUDENT LOAN DEBT FOR
40 MILLION PEOPLE COME UP TO
$50,000 A POP, PLUS MAKING
PUBLIC COLLEGE TUITION FREE.
WHICH SHE SAYS WOULD BE FUNDED
BY A TAX ON ULTRA MILLIONAIRES
WHO SHE HAS GOT A MESSAGE FOR.
>> YOU ARE PROTECTED IN YOUR
FACTORIES WITH FIREFIGHTERS AND
POLICE OFFICERS THAT ALL OF US
HELPED TO PAY.
WE SAY, "GOOD FOR YOU, THAT YOU
HAVE NOW GOTTEN THIS GREAT
FORTUNE.
BUT, TWO SENT TOES -- PAY BACK
SO EVERYBODY ELSE GETS A
CHANCE."
>> WARREN AND TARA SAID LAST
NIGHT THEY SUPPORT EFFORTS IN
THE HOUSE TO TRY
G■
AND IMPEACH PRESIDENT TRUMP.
MELISSA CUSTOM XP ONE FOR MORE
ON ALL THE SPLITS BRING ABOUT
QSAR, EDITOR AND
CHIEF
EDITOR IN CHIEF OF
THE HILL.
LET'S TALK ABOUT JOE BIDEN DOING
THE VIDEO ANNOUNCED ON
WEDNESDAY.
GOING IN MAKING THAT APPEARANCE.
LICKING THE PARENTS PERSONALLY.
WHAT YOU THINK OF THAT?
>> DIRECTION OF MINE IS,
"FINALLY."
HE HAS BEEN HEMMING AND HAWING.
I RAN INTO A MONOPLANE LAST FALL
AND HE SAID HE WOULD MAKE A
DECISION.
HE HAS CONTINUALLY POSTPONED IT.
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT, THE LAST
COUPLE MONTHS HE'S BEEN RUNNING.
HE ASSEMBLED A TEAM.
MELISSA, I THINK WILL BE
FASCINATING TO SEE WHERE HE
STANDS ON MEDICARE FOR ALL, ON
THE GREEN NEW DEAL, ON A FREE
TUITION.
ABOLISH ICE.
ALL THESE THINGS OF THE LEFT
WANTS.
WHERE DO YOU STAND?
>> Melissa: THERE IS SOME ROOM
IN THEIR TO BE THE PERSON WHO IS
NOT LUNGING TO THE LEFT.
IF YOU SAW THE CATALOG OF
SOUND BITES HE PLAYED AHEAD OF
TIME, IT SEEMS LIKE AS THEY
SCOOT FURTHER AND FURTHER, THERE
IS THIS OPEN FIELD ON THE OTHER
SO HE CAN WALK INTO.
THE QUESTION BECOMES IF YOU
DON'T EMBRACE THOSE THINGS, DO
YOU GET OUT OF THE PRIMARY ON
TOP?
>> THAT'S A FASCINATING THING
I'M LOOKING FOR.
WILL HE SAY, "WE CAN'T DO ALL
THIS.
WE CAN'T AFFORD IT, WE CAN DO
BOLD THINGS, BUT WE HAVE TO PICK
A SPOT."
REMEMBER, MEDICARE FOR ALL
DOESN'T HAVE THE VOTES IN THE
CONGRESS, NEVER DOES THE GREEN
NEW DEAL PAID WITH A BACKLASH BE
SEVERE FROM THE LEFT?
WITHOUT A DOUBT, THE PARTY HAS
MOVED LEFT.
BERNIE SANDERS WROTE THE
PLATFORM IN 2016 AND NOW, AS HE
SAYS, THEY ARE MORE MAINSTREAM.
BERNIE SANDERS OF COURSE IS TO
THE LEFT OF MOST OF THE PAR÷■÷■g
SEEMS TO AUTHENTICALLY STICK
WHEREVER IT IS THAT HE PUTS DOWN
HIS MARKER AS OPPOSED TO THOSE
WHO WILL BE QUESTIONED ABOUT,
"YOU USED TO BELIEVE THIS AND I
SAVED YOU BELIEVE THIS.
HOW SINCERE DO WE THINK YOU
MORE?"
EVEN WHEN PRESSED REPLACE THE
SOUND BITE
ABOUT THE BUS AND THERE IS A
BUMMER.
HAS
THE HE SAYS HE HAS WRITTEN A LOT
OF OPPOSITION ADS IN HIS TIME IN
THE SENATE.
SOMEONE ASKED HIM ABOUT THEIR
FAMILY WHO LEFT SOVIET RUSSIA
AND THEIR EXPERIENCE WITH
SOCIALISM AND COMMUNISM.
HE WAS THE QUESTION AND ANSWER.
>> MY FAMILY LEFT SOVIET RUSSIA
IN 1979 FLEEING FROM SOME OF THE
VERY SAME SOCIALIST POLICIES YOU
SEEM EAGER TO IMPLEMENT IN THIS
COUNTRY.
MY QUESTION IS HOW YOU RECTIFY
YOUR NOTION OF DEMOCRATIC
SOCIALISM WITH THE FAILURES OF
SOCIALISM IN NEARLY EVERY
COUNTRY THAT HAS TRIED IT.
>> IS IT YOUR ASSUMPTION THAT I
SUPPORTED OR BELIEVE IN A FAIR
TRAIN COMMUNISM THAT EXISTED IN
SOVIET UNION?
I DON'T.
I OPPOSED IT.
I BELIEVE IN A VIGOROUS
DEMOCRACY.
>> Melissa: WHAT DID YOU THINK
OF THAT ANSWER?
>> BERNIE SANDERS IS GOOD.
HE HAS BEEN IN CONGRESS AND T
IN■ ANS■L■LNLM■@■@ERIN THAT SITN
AT HALL.■L■L■L■L■L■L■L THINK T■E
HELPED THEM.
IT'S GOING TO BE FASCINATING TO
SEE THE DYNAMIC BETWEEN HIM AND
BERNIE SANDERS.
THEY ARE TWO ELDER STATEMENT IN
THE PARTY.
THEY OVERLAPPED IN THE SENATE
FOR TWO YEARS.
BUT THEY HAVE BEEN DIAMETRICALLY
OPPOSED ON A NUMBER OF ISSUES,
WHETHER IT WAS0L THE, THE
IRAQ WAR.
BERNIE COULD GO A ON
■■■■■ FRONTS.
MOSTLY POSITIVE, AS HE DID IN
2016.
I THINK THAT DYNAMIC BETWEEN THE
TWO MEN IS GOING TO BE ONE TO
WATCH IN THE COMING MONTHS.
>> Melissa: IN THE MEANTIME,
POURING A LOT OF COLD WATER ON
THE WHOLE ENTIRE THING,
MITCH MCCONNELL TALKING ABOUT
HOW HE WOULD WELCOME THIS
SOCIALISM.
LOOK AT THIS.
>> THE MAJORITY OF THE SENATE
NEXT YEAR, NONE OF THOSE THINGS
ARE GOING TO PASS THE SENTENCE.
THEY WON'T EVEN BE VOTED ON.
SO THINK OF ME AS THE GRIM
REAPER.
[LAUGHTER]
BECAUSE I AM GOING TO MAKE SURE
THAT SOCIALISM DOESN'T LAND ON
THE PRESIDENT'S DESK.
>> Melissa: I MEAN, IS THAT
GOOD FOR REPUBLICANS?
GRIM REAPER -- DO SOUND LIKE YOU
ARE OLD AND OLD-FASHIONED IN THE
OLD PARTY?
ALL THE KIDS LIKE THE NEWFANGLED
STUFF.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST TIME I'VE
HEARD HER TELL MIKE A POLITICIAN
REFERRED TO HIMSELF AS THE GRIM
REAPER, BUT IT WORKS WITH THE
BASE.
HE HAS FACED PRIMARY CHALLENGES
BEFORE.
I THINK HE IS GOING TO ENDORSE
MITCH MCCONNELL, AND THAT WILL
PREVENT A SCARE OF A
PRIMARY CHALLENGE.
THEN HE LAUGHED AND WERE ABOUT
THE GENERAL AND THE MAJORITY IN
THE SENATE.
THIS IS HIS PAGE.
LISTEN, IF YOU REELECT
REPUBLICANS IN THE SENATE, WE'LL
STOP THESE IDEAS WHICH HE SAYS
ARE CRAZY.
IT'S JUST A FEW PEOPLE -- A LOT
OF PEOPLE IN THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY SUPPORT THEM.
>> Melissa: BOB CUES ACT,
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> THANKS, MELISSA
>> MY POLICE DEPARTMENT AND MY
CLIENTS ALL DESERVE TO HAVE
THEIR REPUTATIONS RESTORED.
THAT'S WHY TODAY WE ARE TAKING
ACTION.
IN FEDERAL COURT, LET ME MAKE
ONE THING PERFECTLY CLEAR.
THE CHICAGO BROTHERS TOLD THE
TRUTH.
>> Melissa: THE BROTHERS
ACCUSED OF ATTACKING
JUSSIE SMOLLETT IN JANUARY HAVE
ANNOUNCED THEY ARE SUING THE
EMPIRE ACTORS ATTORNEYS FOR
DEFAMATION.
HIS LEGAL TEAM HAS SAID THE
BROTHERS CARRIED OUT A VIOLENT
HOMOPHOBIC ATTACK AGAINST THEIR
CLIENTS.
WITH THE BROTHERS ALLEGE THAT
SMOLLETT PAID THEM TO HATEIME.
AND NOW THEY WANT TO RESTORE
THEIR REPUTATIONS.
MIKE TOBIN IS LIVE ON CHICAGO
WITH MORE IN THIS ONE.
IT'S A NEW WRINKLE EVERY DAY.
>> IT GETS COPULATED.
THE ATTACK WAS
HOAXED,
CONCEIVED AS MELISSA MENTIONED,
IT DOES NOT MENTION THE EMPIRE
ACTOR AS A DEFENDANT.
RATHER, THE SUIT IS DIRECTED AT
THE HIGH-PROFILE LEGAL TEAM.
ATTORNEY MARK ERRICO'S DID THE
ROUNDS ON NEWS PROGRAMS AND
PODCASTS
THE SUIT CLAIMS THE LAWYERS SAID
THINGS THAT WERE
FALSE, BLAMING THE ATTACKS ON
THE OSUNDAIRO BROTHERS PRAY THAT
THEY HAD EXECUTED HATE CRIME.
THEY WERE WHITE FACE.
HE CLAIMS THE STATEMENTS WERE
DAMAGING TO THE REPUTATIONS AND
BUSINESS OF THE BROTHERS AND
CAUSE THEM EMOTIONAL DISTRESS.
THEY ARE SEEKING PUNITIVE
DAMAGES AS WELL AS COURT COSTS.
THEIR ATTORNEY GLORIA SCHMIDT
SAYS THE SUIT IS ABOUT CLEARING
THE ROTATION OF THE BROTHERS AS
WELL AS THE CITY OF CHICAGO.
SHE READ A PREPARED STATEMENT
FROM THE BROTHERS.
>> WE HAVE SAT BACK AND WATCHED
LIE AFTER LIE BEING FABRICATED
ABOUT US IN THE METED.
ONLY SO ONE BIG LIE CAN CONTINUE
TO HAVE LIFE.
THESE LIES ARE DESTROYING OUR
CHARACTER AND OUR REPUTATION AND
OUR PERSONAL AND PROFESSIONAL
LIFE.
>> ON APRIL 16TH, ON THE PODCAST
"UNREASONABLE DOUBT," ONE LAWYER
SAID THAT ONE OF THE BROTHERS
ENGAGED IN HOMOSEXUAL ACTS WITH
SMOLLETT.
HE SAID IT'S FALSE.
BACKGROUND
A THEORY FOR WHY THE BROTHERS
WOULD HAVE ATTACKED THE ACTOR IF
IT WAS NOT AT HIS DIRECTION.
AND THE STORY FLOATED BY THE
SOURCE FROM THE SMOLLETT TEAM IS
THAT ONE BROTHER WAS WORRIED THE
OTHER WAS■+ ■ + ■#■#E###■■■E■■ .
>> Melissa: WAS BRINGING THE
FORMERICT ATTORNEY.
F ALL THIS
CASE HAS A CHANCE?
HE IS SUING THE LAWYERS.
WHAT IS THE SIGNIFICANCE OF
THAT?
THEY ARE SUING THE LAWYERS, I■
SHOULD SAY
>> ANY RESPONSIBLE PROSECUTOR
WHO IS GOING TO DISMISS CHARGES
AGAINST SOMEONE LIKE
JUSSIE SMOLLETT REALLY SHOULD
HAVE MADE HIM PAY FULL
RESTITUTION BUT ALSO ADMIT
RESPONSIBILITY.
WHETHER HE HAS TO PLAYED GUILTY
OR
NOT IS NOT THE POINT.
THEREAFTER ADMIT RESPONSIBILITY
AND WE WOULDN'T BE THERE.
THE LAWYERS OR NOBODY ELSE WOULD
BE ABLE TO GO OUT IN THE MEDIA.
AS THIS LAWSUIT HAS ALLEGED, TO
SAY THINGS LIKE THESE GUYS
COMMITTED A CRIMINAL HOMOPHOBIC
ATTACK.
THEY ARE SAYING THAT THOSE WORDS
WERE FALSE AND THAT THEY YOU
DAMAGED THE REPUTATION.
NOW THAT THIS DEFAMATION CASE
MELISSA, THEY
CAN GO INTO COURT AND PROVE THAT
WHAT THEY SAID WAS ACTUALLY
TRUE.
IF THEY CAN.
IF THEY CAN, IT WOULD BE AN
ABSOLUTE DEFENSE.
WHETHER OR NOT THEIR REPUTATION
HAS BEEN HARMED.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT, THESE
GUYS WHO ARE ALLEGED TO HAVE
BEEN -- LET'S JUST CALL IT THE
SHAM, ALLEGED BY THE
PROSECUTORS.
EXCUSE ME, BY THE POLICE
DEPARTMENT IN CHICAGO.
IF THEY WERE PART OF SOME KIND
OF A MUCH MORE COULD
YOU REALISTICALLY DAMAGE THE
REPUTATION?
>> Melissa: WELL, THEY SAY
THEY ARE NOT GF A HATE
CRIME.
THEY ARE GUILTY OF A SHAM CRIME.
SO I GUESS THAT WOULD BE -- THAT
TRYING TO MAKE.CE THAT THEY ARE
WE HAVE -- TO US, THERE'S NOT A
BIG DIFFERENCE.
TO THEM, THERE OBVIOUSLY IS.
IS THERE A CHANCE THAT THROUGH
THIS PROCESS SOMEHOW SMOLLETT IS
FORCED TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY,
AS YOU SAID, IF THAT'S REALLY
WHAT HAPPENED?
BECAUSE HE STILL MAINTAINS THAT
IT'S NOT HOW THINGS WENT DOWN.
THAT HE WAS THE VICTIM IN ALL
THIS.
>> I THINK CLEARLY IF THIS CASE
EVER MAKES ITS WAY INTO THE
COURTROOM OR EVEN INTO
DEPOSITIONS, JUSSIE SMOLLETT MAY
HAVE TO TESTIFY UNDER OATH AS A
WITNESS IN THIS CIVIL CASE.
LET'S KEEP IN MIND, THE CITY OF
CHICAGO IS ALSO GOING AFTER
SMOLLETT CIVILLY.
SO■ IT'S POSSIBLE THAT HIS
VERSION OF THE EVENTS COULD BE
LOCKED DOWN IN SWORN TESTIMONY.
IN EITHER ONE OF THESE TYPES OF
AVENUES.
EVEN THOUGH THE PROSECUTOR, IN
MY OPINION, DROPPED THE BALL BY
NOT MAKING HIM ACCEPT
RESPONSIBILITY IN A CRIMINAL
COURT ROOM, HE MAY VERY WELL
HAVE TO ANSWER TO THIS IN A
CIVIL COURT ROOM.
EVEN IF IT IS AS A WITNESS FOR
EITHER THE PLAINTIFFS OR THE
DEFENDANTS IN THIS DEFAMATION
LAWSUIT.
>> Melissa: THAT WOULD BE THE
GAME CHANGER.
IF HE WAS BROUGHT INTO A
COURTROOM OR DEPOSITION
TYPESETTING AND HE HAD TO SAY
UNDER OATH WHAT HAPPENED.
HE WOULD HAVE TO MAKE THE CHOICE
IF YOU LIES UNDER OATH OR
CONTINUES WITH HIS STAR IF, IN
FACT, IT IS FALSEHOOD.
AT THAT POINT HE WOULD FACE THE
CONSEQUENCES, IF HE CONTINUES TO
LIE CUSTOMER GOURD YOU HAVE TOAD
IT STILL KEEPS GOING?
>> RIGHT.
IN MY OPINION, THESE LAWYERS ON
HIS BEHALF SHOULD HAVE TAKEN
THEIR SWEETHEART DISMISSAL AND
JUST GOT HOME AND BEEN THANKFUL
FOR IT.
INSTEAD THEY WENT OUT ACCORDING
TO THIS LAWSUIT AND MADE VARIOUS
MEDIA APPEARANCES WHERE THEY
SAID THESE THINGS ALLEGED TO BE
FALSE AND DEFAMATORY.
BY GETTING JUSSIE SMOLLETT IN
COURT AS A WITNESS, HE IS NOT
GOING TO BE ABLE TO HIDE BEHIND
PAID SPOKESPERSONS.
BECAUSE AFTER THE CASES ARE
OVER, THAT IS ESSENTIALLY WHAT
THE LAWYERS ARE.
THEY ARE A P.R. TEAM FOR
JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
THEY WILL BE ABLE TO HIDE BEHIND
THAT.
IF HE HAS TO GO INTO COURT UNDER
OATH AND TESTIFY, HE'S GOT TO
TELL THE TRUTH.
IF HE DOESN'T COME HE
THEORETICALLY OPEN HIMSELF UP TO
ADDITIONAL PROSECUTION.
>> Melissa: THAT COULD BE THE
BASIS FOR THIS, TRYING TO GET
HIM OUT FROM BEHIND WHAT IS NOW
HIS P.R. TEAM.
VERY INTER■■G■.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US, WE
APPRECIATE IT.
>> HAPPY TO BE HERE ANY TIME.
>> Melissa: THE TERM IN THE
ADMINISTRATION AND THE HIGHEST
COURT IN THE LAND AS JUSTICES
CONSIDER WHETHER TO ADD A
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION TO THE 2020
CENSUS.
A LIVE REPORT ON THE BATTLE
BREWING IN THE SUPREME COURT.
PLUS, HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE
CHAIR JERRY NADLER SUBPOENAS
FORMER WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL DON
BEGAN TO TESTIFY BEFORE
CONGRESS.
LEGITIMATE OVERSIGHT, OR ARE
DEMOCRATS BUYING POLITICS
CUSTOMER CONGRESSMAN
DARRELL ISSAvalue.
Thank You, Admiral.
So if you need money for your
family,
call NewDay USA.
Need cash?
At NewDay, veteran homeowners
can get
$54,000 dollars or more
to conso■÷■÷te credit
card debt
and lower their payments by $600
every month.
0G$ç)FMNnDv-B0.H#ú$DP;n.úUn&>Xqi
When you start with a better
hot dog from Oscar Mayer...
That ...you can do no wrong....
Where did you learn that?
The internet...
Yeah?
MMM!
With no artificial preservatives
or added nitrates or nitrites,
it's all for the love
of hot dogs.
My joi
The pain and swelling.
The psoriasis.
COSENTYX treats more
than just the joint pain
of active psoriatic arthritis.
It even helps stop further
joint damage.
if y Before starting, get
checked for tuberculosis.
An increisk ofÑ=ctions?■t
them may occur.
Tell your doctor about an
infection or symptoms,
if your inflammatory
bowel disease symptoms
develop or worsen,
or if you've had a vaccine
or plan to.
Serious alle reacy occ.
Get real relief, with COSENTYX.
You're turning onto the
street
c c
when you barely
clip a passing car.
Minor accident
—no big deal, right?
Wrong. Your insurance
company is gonna raise
your rate after the other
car got a scratch so small
you coulda fixed
it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that
pen and use it to sign up
with a different
insurance company.
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because of
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>> Melissa: >> Melissa: A
SUMMIT BETWEEN NORTH KOREAN
LEADER KIM JONG UN
AND RUSSIAN
PRESIDENT VLADIMIR PUTIN THIS AT
THE TAKE PLACE ON THURSDAY.
THIS IS ACCORDING TO A KREMLIN
OFFICIAL.
THE TWO ARE EXPECTED TO MEET IN
EASTERN RUSSIA ALONG ITS PACIFIC
COAST.
RUSSIAN NEWS AGENCIES REPORT
THAT THE TALKS WILL CENTER ON
NORTS NUCLEAR PROGRAM.
AND A FOX NEWS ALERT, HOUSE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN
JERRY NADLER HAS SUBPOENAED
FORMER WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL
DON MCGAHN, CALLING ON HIM TO
TESTIFY PUBLICLY NEXT MONTH ON
POTENTIAL OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE
RELATED INCIDENTS OUTLINED IN
THE MUELLER REPORT.
HOGAN GIDLEY SAYS THAT DEMOCRATS
ARE GETTING DESPERATE.
>> DEMOCRATS LIKE JERRY NADLER
CONTINUE TO TRY AND ATTACK THIS
PRESIDENT AND ATTACK MEMBERS OF
THIS ADMINISTRATION REPEATEDLY.
HE IS NOT GOING TO LEARN
ANYTHING ELSE ABOUT DON MCGAHN
OR THIS ADMINISTRATION THAT
BOB MUELLER DIDN'T FIND IN TWO
YEARS OF WASTED TIME AND ENERGY.
THE ONLY THING HE'S GOING TO
AGAIN, QUITE FRANKLY, OUR MAY BE
SOME POLITICAL ALLIES OF THE FA■
LEFT WHO ARE CONSPIRACY■■■■■r■■T
SOMEHO WAS A SHA■■■■■
■&&■■■>■>■>p>■>p>p>■>■>■>■>■>■>■
THE QUESTION DDD■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■D
LE■■DD■■■■■■■■■■■■PECIAL COUNSE,
WHICH HAD ALL Ol■ORYççç■■■■■ SPT
■d■■VEVIS.
B■■■■E
SECOND.
FIRST OF ALL, SOME■■■ NEWS MADEA
LITTLE WHILE AGO.
JARED KUSHNER WEIGHING IN FOR
THE FIRST TIME ON THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION AT THAT TIME 100
FORM.
BOB MUELLER'S INTEREST IN
JARED KUSHNER WAS THAT JUNE 9TH
2016 MEETING WITH THE WOMAN ON
THE LEFT.
A RUSSIAN ATTORNEY.
IN THE REPORT, HE SAID THAT
INVESTIGATORS CONSIDERED WHETHER
THAT MAY HAVE CONSTITUTED AN
ILLEGAL FOREIGN CAMPAIGN
CONTRIBUTION BUT ULTIMATELY
DECIDED THEY COULD NOT DETERMINE
WHETHER SHE WAS OFFERING
ANYTHING OF VALUE.
HERE IS WHAT KUSHNER SAID ABOUT
HIS PARTICIPATION WITH THE
OFFICE AND SPECIAL COUNSEL.
LISTEN HERE.
>> WHEN THE WHOLE NOTION OF THE
RUSSIA COLLUSION NARRATIVE CAME
UP, I WAS THE FIRST PERSON TO
SAY I'M HAPPY TO PARTICIPATE
WITH ANY INVESTIGATIONS.
AT THIS POINT I'VE DONE THREE
HOUSE INTERVIEWS, ABOUT NINE
HOURS WITH THE SPECIAL COUNSEL.
IF YOU LOOK AT MY STATEMENT FROM
JULY, I PUT OUT ABOUT 12 PAGES
OF STATEMENT EXPLAINING THESE
DIFFERENT THINGS.
I THINK EVERYTHING I SAID IS
PROVEN TO BE TRUE AND IT'S BEEN
VERY THOROUGHLY INVESTIGATED.
THE ONE THING THE MUELLDDDDDDD@E
RUSSIA COLLUSION HAV■■■■■■■■■■■N
DEMOCRACY FOR MORE■■ THAN RUSSIA
AT THE SAME TIME AT THAT GOING
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
WHITE HOUSE ON HOW THEY WILL
RESPOND TO THE SUBPOENA ISSUED
YESTERDAY BY JERROLD NADLER TO
GET DON MCGAHN, THE FORMER
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL, UP IN FRONT
OF HIS COMMITTEE.
IN A STATEMENT, JERROLD NADLER'S
INCOME "DON McCANN IS A
CRITICAL WITNESS TO MANY OF THE
ALLEGED INCIDENCES OF
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE AND OTHER
MISCONDUCT DESCRIBED IN THE
MUELLER REPORT."
CENTRAL ISSUE IS WHETHER THE
PRESIDENT CAN ASSERT EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE AND PREVENT DONE
MCGANN FROM TESTIFYING.
THE PRESIDENT DID NOT EXERT A
NEGATIVE PRIVILEGE OVER RELEASES
OF PART OF THE MUELLER REPORT
THAT INCLUDED TESTIMONY FROM
DON MCGAHN, THERE WAS NO
ATTORNEY-CLIENT PRIVILEGE AND AM
TO GO BACK AND MAKE THAT CHANGE
NOW WOULD BE PROBLEMATIC IN
COURT.
THERE IS AA÷ SENIOR
WHITE HOUSE AIDES REFUSING TO
TESTIFY BEFORE CONGRESS.
FIRST AND FOREMOST AMONG THEM IS
CARL KLEIN WHO WAS THE FORMER
DIRECTOR OF THE WHITE HOUSE
OFFICE OF PERSONNEL SECURITY.
HE WAS SUPPOSED TO GIVE A
DEPOSITION TODAY ON
CAPITOL HILL.
HE WAS TOLD BY THE WHITE HOUSE
TO IGNORE THE SUBPOENA AND NOW
ELIJAH CUMMINGS, THE CHAIRMAN OF
THE HOUSE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE,
IS THREATENING TO HOLD THEM IN
CONTEMPT.
MICHAEL FLYNN ALSO DID NOT
TESTIFY, NEITHER DID KARL ROVE
DURING THE BUSH■=■=■=■=■=■=■=■==
GOINGRLY■1■u■u■u■u■u■u■u■u■u■u■Y
KISSINGER.
THERE'S ALSO A RICH HISTORY OF
AIDS, EVEN PRESIDENTS,
TESTIFYING BEFORE CONGRESS.
INCLUDING GERALD FORD, WHO BACK
IN 1974 APPEARED BEFORE CONGRESS
TO TALK ABOUT HIS PARDON OF
NIXON.
PAT BUCHANAN AND AL HAIG
TESTIFIED ABOUT WATERGATE,
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISORS,
SPECIAL COUNSEL TO
PRESIDENT CLINTON, A NUMBER OF
CLINTON-ERA STAFF MEMBERS WHO
TESTIFIED, ALL THE WAY UP TO
STEVE BANNON FROM THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION WHO TESTIFIED
AFTER HE WAS DELIVERED A
SUBPOENA TO APPEAR BEFORE
CONGRESS.
BACK IN 2,080 FEDERAL JUDGE
RULED THAT THEN-BUSH WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL HARRIET MIERS AND THE
CHIEF OF STAFF, JOSH BOLDEN,
WERE NOT IMMUNE FROM
CONGRESSIONAL SUBPOENAS, EITHER.
THEY GOT TO COME UP, MELISSA,
WITH SOMETHING VERY CREATIVE
HERE AT THE WHITE HOUSE IN ORDER
FOR A JUDGE TO SAY, "YOU ARE
RIGHT, McGAHN SHOULD NOT
COMPLY WITH THAT SUBPOENA."
HIS TESTIFY IS SCHEDULED.
WE'LL SEE WHAT■■APPENS.
>> Melissa: NEED A FANTASTIC
JOB SETTING THE TABLE FOR US AND
WE APPRECIATE IT.
LET'S GET THE DISCUSSION THAT HE
SET UP.
FORMER COVERS MATERIAL ICE IS
WITH US.
HE'S A REPUBLICAN FROM
CALIFORNIA WHO OF COURSE SERVED
ON THE HOUSE JUDICIARY AND
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEES.
SARAH, THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
FIRST OF ALL, DO YOU THINK THAT
McGAHN SHOULD APPEAR OR
REFUSE?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> CLEARLY HE WILL APPEAR.
WHEN I THINK IS IMPORTANT --
BECAUSE YOU SET UP A NUMBER OF
THESE, THE BATES DECISION WHICH
OCCURRED UNDER PRESIDENT BUSH
AND THEN AMY BERMAN JACKSON IN
THE FAST AND FURIOUS CASE THAT
HE CURED UNDER OBAMA, THOSE MAKE
IT CLEAR TO THE WHITE HOUSE
CAN'T FEEL THE SENSE OF BUDDY.
WHAT'S BEING ARGUED RIGHT NOW --
AND YOU'VE MENTIONED THE NO
-SHOW TODAY, IS THAT
ELIJAH CUMMINGS -- AND IT'S
TRADITION, BUT IT'S A BAD
TRADITION -- HE WANTS TO GET
SOMEBODY IN A DEPOSITION WHO IS
A CURRENT REPRESENTATIVE OF THE
EXECUTIVE BRANCH, LAWYERS FROM
EXECUTIVE BRANCH.
MANY PEOPLE WHO CAN ASSERT WHY
SOMETHING SHOULDN'T BE ANSWERED.
IN THE LAST DAYS OF THE LAST
CONGRESS, DEMOCRATS HAD NO
PROBLEM INSISTING THAT THE
PEOPLE FROM AMA
ADMION ANDERS HAVE
THAT REPRESENTATION, INCLUDING
JAMES COMEY WIN AGAIN.
INCLUDING PETER STRZOK.
IT'S INTERESTING HOW
ELIJAH CUMMINGS WANTS IT ONE WAY
WHEN HE WANTS A WITNESS NOT TO
HAVE COUNSEL, AND THE OTHER WAY
BOTTOM LINE, DON IS A VERY SMART
LAWYER.
HE'S ALREADY TESTIFIED.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN OPEN AND
TRANSPARENT IN THE WAY THOSE TWO
PREVIOUS PRESIDENTS WERE NOT.
SO EXPECT THEM TO COME BUT I
EXPECTED TO INSIST ON HAVING
PEOPLE BEHIND HIM THAT CAN
ADVISE HIM AS TO WHEN TO ANSWER
QUESTION AND WHEN A PRIVILEGE
MIGHT BE APPROPRIATE.
>> Melissa: HOW BIG OF A RISK
DO YOU THINK IT IS?
WE KNOW EXACTLY WHAT THE
QUESTIONERS WOULD BE GOING
AFTER.
THEY ARE TRYING TO PURSUE
OBSTRUCTION.
THEY ARE TRYING TO SET UP THE
POSSIBILITY, THE GROUNDS, FOR
IMPEACHMENT.
DON MCGAHN HAS ALREADY BEEN
THROUGH 30 HOURS OF QUESTIONING
IN FRONT OF ME WOULD.
HE HAS ANSWERED THE WAY HE HAS
ANSWERED.
IS THERE MUCH RISK AT HIM GOING,
OR COULD HE JUST COME OUT AND
OSTENSIBLY REPEAT BASICALLY WHAT
HE SAID BEFORE?
>> YOU SAID IT VERY WELL.
■■■■■■■ HE WAS
THOUGHTFUL AND WHAT HE SAID AND
HOW HE SAID IT.
HE WILL REPEAT WHAT HE SAID.
THIS IS AN EXAMPLE OF EVERYTHING
HAVING BEEN SAID BUT NOT
EVERYBODY HAS SAID IT.
IN THE CASE OF JERRY NADLER AND
ELIJAH CUMMINGS, THE TWO
CHAIRMAN, THEY WANT TO HAVE A
POLITICAL SHOW.
THEY WANT TO HAVE THAT LIVE
THEATER.
THAT MAY BE POLITICALLY FINE BUT
IT WON'T CHANGE A LEGAL DECISION
THAT WAS NOT JUST MADE BY
MUELLER BUT CODIFIED BY THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL OF THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE.
>> Melissa: BUT THAT'S THE
LEGAL DECISION.
WHAT THEY ARE TRYING TO DO IS TO
SET THE TABLE FOR IMPEACHMENT.
>>  >> EXACTLY.
>> Melissa: SO HE DOES COME,
HE SITS DOWN, AND HE SAYS WAS
EXPECTED AND DOESN'T GO FURTHER.
THEN HE JUST REITERATES THE
POINTS THAT WERE MADE BY MUELLER
AND THOSE TEN POINTS OF POSSIBLE
OBSTRUCTION.
IS THAT ENOUGH IN AND OF ITSELF?
FOR THEM THE HOUSE TO GO AHEAD
AND MOVE FORWARD ON IMPEACHMENT?
>> IN THE CASE OF MANY PEOPLE IN
THE HOUSE, AFC, JERRY NADLER,
AND A FEW OTHERS WHO HAVE MADE
STATEMENTS THAT CAN BE REPEATED
ON THE AIR, THIS POLITICAL
DECISION HAS ALREADY BEEN MADE.
THEY ARE READY TO IMPEACH THE
PRESIDENT.
IT'S A POLITICAL STATEMENT.
BUT THERE'S A BIG DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A POLITICAL STATEMENT IN
A LEGAL STATEMENT.
THE FORMER PRESIDENT,
BILL CLINTON, LOST HIS BAR
LICENSE FOR PERJURY.
FOR LYING UNDER OATH.
THAT DID NOT CHANGE THE FACT
THAT AT THE END OF THE DATE THE
POLITICAL DECISION WAS NOT TO
REMOVE HIM FROM OFFICE.
THEY COULD HAVE THIS DISCUSSION
IN A PURELY POLITICAL FASHION
BUT THE LEGAL DECISION THAT HE
DID NOTHING LEGALLY WRONG HAS
BEEN MADE.
I THINK THAT THE IMPORTANT
THING.
THIS IS PURELY POLITICAL NOW.
THE BIG QUESTION IS, WILL THE
NEW MAJORITY IN THE HOUSE
VIOLATE PEOPLE'S RIGHT TO HAVE
COUNSEL?
>> Melissa: CONGRESSMAN,
THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME.
A MAJOR SUPREME COURT CASE AS
JUSTICES WEIGHED THE TRUMP
ADMISSIONS PLAN TO ADD A
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION TO THE 2020
CENSUS.
THE FIRE FROM REACHING
IMPLICATIONS THIS COULD HAVE ON
IMMIGRATION AND MORE.
WHEN WE HEAR FROM THE FORMER
CHIEF OF CITIZENSHIP.
THAT'S NEXT.
♪ ♪
Ok everyone!
Our mission is to
provide complete,
balanced nutrition
for strength and energy!
Whoo-hoo!
tasting Ensure.
With nine grams of protein
and twenty-six vitamins
and minerals.
Ensure, for strength
and energy.
Fact is, every insurance company
hopes you drive safely.■nW÷÷
with Drivewise.
It lets you know when you go too
fast...
...and brake too hard.
With feedback to help you drive
safer.
Giving you the power to actually
lower your cost.
Unfortunatelñt do
anything about that.
Now that you know the truth...
are you in Good Hands?
■■■■■■■■■ñ/■/
Shaving has been difficult for
me.
I have very sensitive skin, and
I get ingrowing hairs.
So it's a daunting task.
Oh I love it. It's a great
razor.
It has that 'fence' in the
middle.
It gives a nice smooth shave.
Just stopping that irritation...
That burn that I get is really
life changing.
♪♪
This is the family who booked
the flight,
who saved by adding a hotel,
which led to new adventures,■
that captured their
imaginationsO
♪♪■
and turned moments into
memories.
With flights,    activitie
for  you need to go.ation,
>> Melissa: FOX NEWS ALERT,
PARTISAN LINES DRAWN AS THE
SUPREME COURT JUSTICES HEAR
ARGUMENTS OVER PLANS TO ADD A
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION TO TG■
CENSUS AND PROTESTERS ARE
VOICING THEIR OPPOSITION ON
THE STEPS OUTSIDE THE
SUPREME COURT.
DOUG McKELWAY IS THERE WITH
MORE.
DOUG?
>> MELISSA, OCCURRING AS THIS
DOES ADMITS THE HEATED DEBATE
OVER?■ç■ç■ç■ç■ç■ç■ç■ç■ç■■MM?■ç■■
ç■ç■?■ç■?■ç■?■?■ç■?■ç■?■ç■ç■?■çL
ARGUMENT SINCEn MORNING HAS
TAKEN O SIGNIFICANCE.
IT CENTERS AROUND ONE SIMPLE
LITTLE QUESTION THAT THE TRUMPET
MENSURATION WANTS TO INCLUDE IN
THE 2020 CENSUS, AND THAT
ON IS, "IS THIS PERSON A
CITIZEN OF THE UNITED STATES?"
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S AN UNUSUAL
QUESTION.
IT HAD BEEN INCLUDED IN THE
CENSUS FOR WELL OVER A CENTURY.
ALMOST TWO CENTURIES, FROM 1820
TO 1950.
THE TRUMPET WANTS TO INCLUDE IT
AGAIN BECA BELIEVES IT'S
WHILE THEYç■ç■■ç■ç■ç■ç■ç■ç■ç■ç■S
FOR PARTICIPATING IN THE CENSUS,
THEY REJECT THE LAW THAT HAS
PRINTED ON THE CENSUS WEBSITE
WOULD SAYS, AND I QUOTE, "IT'S
ILLEGAL FOR THE CENSUS BUREAU
TO PUBLISH ANY PRIVATE
INFORMATION THAT IDENTIFIES ANY
INDIVIDUALS OR BUSINESSES."
>> WELL, YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE A
CONSPIRACY THEORIST TO BE
CONCERNED THAT IF THAT DATA IS
OUT THERE, HE COULD POSE A RISK
TO YOU.
WE'VE SEEN ADMINISTRATIONS THAT
IS STICKING PEOPLE UP IN
SENSITIVE PLACES LIKE
COURTHOUSES, SCHOOLS, GOING TO
THE DOCTOR'S OFFICE.
>> EVEN UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT
ACKNOWLEDGES THAT AS MANY AS
6.5 MILLION PEOPLE MIGHT NOT
PARTICIPATE IN THE 2020 CENSUS
IF THAT QUESTION WERE TO BE
INCLUDED.
BY THE WAY, IT IS ILLEGAL NOT TO
FILL OUT A CENSUS.
CENSUS, I SHOULD SAY.
IT'S PUNISHABLE BY A $150 FINE.
THE RAMIFICATIONS OF ANOTHER
ACCOUNT ARE HUGE.
THE CENSUS DETERMINES FOR THE
NEXT TEN YEARS HOW MANY
ELECTORAL VOTES THE STATE HAS.
HOW MANY REPRESENTATIVES THE
STATE HAS, AND NO FEDERAL
RESOURCES ARE DIVVIED OUT TO THE
STATES.
PARTISAN LINES DEVELOP QUICKLY
HERE IN ORAL ARGUMENTS BEFORE
LEFT-LEANING JUSTICES PRESS THE
LAWYER FOR THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT TO EXPLAIN THE
REASONING BEHIND THE CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION.
THEY CITED THE POTENTIAL FOR A
6.5 MILLION PERSON UNDERCOUNT.
CONSERVATIVE JUSTICES ASKED
WHETHER THE CITIZENSHIP QUESTION
ALONE WOULD CAUSE INACCURATE
CENSUS.
CHIEF JUSTICE JOHN ROBERTS
NOTING THAT A RANGE OF QUESTIONS
IS ASKED IN THE CENSUS ANYWAY,
INCLUDING A PERSON'S AGE AND SE
SEX.
THEY WILL HAVE TO RULE BEFORE
THE END OF DO NOT ONLY TO AT
TRADITIONAL DEADLINE BUT TO MEET
THE DEADLINE OF THE PRINTING
OFFICE PAID THEREAFTER BE
PRINTED OUT BY THAT DATE IN
ORDER TO MEET THE CENSUS, WHICH
GETS UNDERWAY INKK■■G■ OF 2020.
BACK TO YOU, MELISSA.
>> Melissa: DOUG, THANK YOU
FOR THAT.
FOR MORE, LET'S BRING IT UP ONCE
I GET THERE.
HE IS FORMER CHIEF OF THE U.S.
OFFICE OF CITIZENSHIP UNDER
PRESIDENT GEORGE W. BUSH.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
LET ME ASK A BASIC QUESTION TO
START.
DO YOU THINK YOU GET A MORE
ACCURATE PICTURE OF WHAT IS
GOING ON AND WHO IS HERE
EXACTLY, AND WITH THE
DEMOGRAPHICS ARE WITH THE
QUESTION THERE?
OR WITHOUT IT?
>> IT'S HARD TO SAY.
INITIALLY I THOUGHT IT WASN'T A
GOOD IDEA TO INCLUDE THE
QUESTION.
BASED ON WHAT EXPERTS ARE SAYING
THAT IT COULD DISSUADE
UNDOCUMENTED IMMIGRANTS FROM
PARTICIPATING IN THE CENSUS.
BUT WHEN I LOOK AND DELVE INTO
THE ISSUE, LOOK AT THE DATA,
IT'S BASED ON FOCUS GROUPS,■ET T
REPRESENTATIVE OF THE GENERAL
POPULATION.
SO THERE IS NO HARD EVIDENCE TO
DETERMINE THAT UNDOCUMENTED
IMMIGRANTS WOULD NOT PARTICIPAT
PARTICIPATE.
I THINK THAT IF THE SENSE      S
ASSETS STAY ON THE FORM, BUT
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE SHARED WITH
LAW ENFORCEMENT.
AND THAT IS INFORMED, THERE'S A
GOOD EDUCATIONAL CAMPAIGN TO THE
PUBLIC ABOUT THAT.
I DON'T SEE WHY IMMIGRANTS AND
UNDOCUMENTED IMMIGRANTS WOULD
NOT WANT TO PARTICIPATE.
I THINK THIS IS JUST ANOTHER
OPPORTUNITY BY DEMOCRATS TO
TOTALLY POLITICIZE AN ISSUE AND
ATTACK DONALD TRUMP.
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS WE'VE
ASKED -- WE HAVE HAD A
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION DURING THE
OBAMA YEARS IN THE■JñJéééé■ééééA
TOOL THAT IS DONE -- AN
INSTRUMENT THAT IS DONE EVERY
SINGLE YEAR -- THERE IS A
QUESTION ABOUT CITIZENSHIP.
>> Melissa: WAS THERE LESS
PARTICIPATION ON THAT ONE?
>> YES.
>> Melissa: IN ESSENCE, THAT
IS PROOF THAT FEW PEOPLE WOULD
RESPOND IF THE Q WAS
THERE.
I WONDER IF YOU ARE HERE
ILLEGALLY IF YOU RESPOND TO THE
CENSUS AT ALL, WITH THE QUESTION
IS THERE OR NOT.
BEING WORRIED THAT YOU ARE JUST
BEING WATCHED FROM SOMEWHERE AND
YOU ARE NOT HERE LEGALLY.
I WANT TO BRING YOU TO SOME
BREAKING NEWS RIGHT NOW THAT WE
ARE SEEING.
THERE IS SOME NEW VIDEO WE HAVE
IN, SHOWING ARMED SMUGGLERS THAT
ARE ESCORTING A MIGRANT FAMILY
OVER THE BORDER IN ARIZONA.
THIS VIDEO CAME FROM U.S. BORDER
PATROL SURVEILLANCE CAMERAS AND
IT IS FROM SATURDAY NIGHT.
IT'S NEAR THE TOWN OF LUCASVILLE
IN THE SOUTHWESTERN CORNER OF
ARIZONA
YOU'RE LOOKING AT FOR TO FIVE
MEN IN TACTICAL GEAR AND MASKS
CARRYING LONG GUNS AND AK-47
ASSAULT RIFLES.
THEY ARE ESCORTING A GOAL
GUATEMALAN WOMAN AND HER CHILD
UNDER A BARRIER.
THIS VIDEO WAS OSTENSIBLY PUT UP
BECAUSE BORDER PATROL WANTS
PEOPLE TO KNOW WHAT THEY ARE
SEEING.
THEY ARE SAYING THIS SHOWS AN
ESCALATION IN THE WAY THAT
PEOPLE ARE CROSSING THE BORDER.
THAT THEY APPREHENDED ALMOST 400
GUATEMALAN IMMIGRANTS ON SEVERAL
BUSES JUST A HUNDRED YARDS FROM
WHERE THIS WAS, RIGHT NEAR THIS
AREA.
THEY ALSO ADD THAT DISEASES
SMUGGLERS IN GENERAL CHARGE
BASICALLY $7,000, IN THEIR
EXPERIENCE, TO TRANSPORT
GUATEMALANS OVER THE BORDER
HERE.
SO THEY CAN APPLY FOR ASYLUM.
WHAT IS YOUR REACTION TO THISÑ@■
I THINK THAT, YES, COYOTES,
SMUGGLERS, THEY ARE ARMING UP.
IF THERE IS ANY QUESTION THAT
THERE'S A CRISIS OF THE BORDER,
I FIGURE THIS VIDEO ILLUSTRATES
THAT THERE IS A CRISIS.
THAT SMUGGLERS ARE WILLING TO
ESCORT THIS INDIVIDUAL TRYING TO
ENTER IRREGULARLY, ILLEGALLY
COME INTO THE COUNTRY.
WITH WEAPONS.
THIS IS SCARY.
THE AMOUNT OF PEOPLE THAT ARE
TRYING TO ENTER ILLEGALLY
THROUGH THE BORDER HAS GONE UP
DRAMATICALLY.
>> Melissa: BUT THIS IS AN
ESCALATION?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
BUT REMEMBER, DEMOCRATS WERE
SAYING COUPLE MONTHS AGO THERE
WAS NO CRISIS OF THE BORDER.
>> Melissa: ABSOLUTELY.
THANK YOU FOR GOING WITH US ON
THE NEWS THAT CAME IN.
HAVE TO CUT IT SHORT NOW.
ANY WARNING FROM A TOP OFFICIAL
IN SRI L FOLLOWING THE
EASTER BOMBING THAT LEFT MORE
THAN 300 PEOPLE DEAD, INCLUDING
SEVERAL AMERICANS.
WE HAVE A LIVE REPORT NEXT.
♪ ♪
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Does this map show the
Peninsula Trail?
You won't find that on a map.
I'll take you there.
Take this left.
If you listen real hard you can
hear the whaleOop.
You hear that?
(VO) Our Subaru Outback
lets us see the world.
Sometimes in ways
we never imagined.
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
What do all these people
have in common, LiMu?
[ guttural grunt ]
Exactly. Nothing!
They're completely
different people.
That's why they
make customized
car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need.
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done it again, LiMu.
[ LiMu grunts ]
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
>> Melissa: FOX NEWS ALERT,
SRI LANKA'S PRIME MINISTER
WARNING THERE ARE MOREOSIVES ANT
THERE AFTER THE EASTER SUICIDE
BOMBINGS KILLED MORE THAN 300
PEOPLE.
THIS COMES AS SRI LANKAN
AUTHORITIES SAY THEY NOW BELIEVE
THE CORRUGATED
BOMBING WAS IN RETALIATION FOR
THE MOSQUE SHOOTINGS.
IN THE MEANTIME, THIS IS NEW
VIDEO FOR ONE OF THE SUSPECTS
WALKING IN AND AROUNDH
MOMENTS BEFORE AN EXPLOSION.
BENJAMIN HALL'S LIVE IN LONDON
BUT MORE.
BENJAMIN?
>> HI, MELISSA.
ALSO TODAY, ISIS TAKING
RESPONSIBILITY FOR THESE
ATTACKS.
THEY DID SO VIA THEIR OFFICIAL
NEWS AGENCY, AND WHILE THEY
OFTEN TAKE RESPONSIBILITY AND
CLAIM CERTAIN ATTACKS IN THE
PAST, IT IS BELIEVED THERE IS A
LINK IN THIS CASE.
FIRST OF ALL, THE SMALL TERROR
GROUP IN SRI LANKA, THE NATIONAL
WAS NEVER THOUGHT TO BE ABLE TO
CARRY  SUCH IN A COORDINATED
AND SOPHISTICAT■8TTACKS SUCH AS
ON T■; OF THIS, OVER 40 SRI
LANKANS WENT TO FIGHT IN IRAQ
AND SYRIA, THE LINK BECOME EVER.
THE DEATH TOLL NOW HAS RISEN■b O
321 IN THE EIGHT BLASTS, WITH
500 INJURED.
TODAY THE PRIME MINISTER
WARNING, AS YOU POINTED OUT,
THAT THERE WERE MORE MILITANTS,
MORE BOMBS OUT THERE.
WE ARE ALSO LEARNING THE
IDENTITY OF THE MASTERMIND BY
THE PLOT.
HE IS SEEN HERE AMONG THE OTHER
SUICIDE BOMBERS BEFORE THE
ATTACK, PLEDGING ALLEGIANCE TO
ISIS LEADERS.
THIS IS A STILL FROM A VIDEO
THAT HAS JUST BEEN RELEASED.
AS YOU POINTED OUT, AS HE S
EARLIER, THAT CHILLING
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO -- ARE POORLY
ONE OF THE SEVEN SUICIDE
BOMBERS --■ CALMLY WALKING IN TE
WEARING THAT HEAVY
BACKPACK, ENTERING SAINT
SEBASTIAN'S CHURCH, WALKING INTO
THE CENTER OF THE
IC Co) THEN
BLoLF UP.
TODAY IN SRI LANKA, FUNERALS
BEGAN AS COMPANY, COUNTRY
OBSERVED A DURNING.
EY ARE UNDER A STATE OF
EMERGENCY IN THE MILITARY IS
OPERATING UNDER ENHANCE WARTIME
POWERS.
SO FAR POLICE HAVE ARRESTED UP
TO 40 PEOPLE IN CONNECTION WITH
THE BOMBING.
THAT WE ARE LEARNING MORE ABOUT
THE DEAD, SPECIFICALLY THE
AMERICANS.
THE FOUR AMERICANS, AMONG THEM
AN 11-YEAR-OLD, A 40-YEAR-OLD
FROM DENVER, NOT PICTURED HERE,
SIBLINGS, 15 AND 19 YEARS OLD.
OTHERS ARE BELIEVED ALSO TO BE
ENTERED.
WE ARE HEARING THERE WILL BE A
SECURITY SHAKE-UP IN S
AFTER IT EMERGED THAT OFFICIALS
DID NOT HEED WARNINGS FROM INDIA
TEN DAYS AGO.
THERE WILL BE SUICIDE ATTACKS ON
CHURCHES AND HOTELS AND THE FBI
NOW SENDING AGENTS TO SRI LANKA
TO IN THE ONGOING
INVESTIGATION.
MELISSA?
>> Melissa: BENJAMIN HALL,
THANK YOU.
NANCY PELOSI PUTTING THE BRAKES
ON IMPEACHMENT, SINGH
INVESTIGATIONS ARE GOOD ENOUGH
FOR NOW.
BY THAT MAY NOT BE ENOUGH FOR
MANY IN OUR CAUCUS.
THE POWER PANEL WEIGHS IN NEXT.
♪ ♪
ly,  call NewDay USA.
A NewDay VA home
loan lets you refinance
your home and take out
54,000 dollars
or more to pay credit card debt,
or just put money in the bank.
It even lowers your payments
by over 600 dollars
a month.
As a veteran, you've
earned the powerful
VA home loan benefit
that lets you
refinance up to 100 percent
of your home's value.
And with home values rising,
that can mean a lot more
money for you and your family.
And because NewDay USA
has been granted
Automatic Authority by the VA,
they can say yes
when banks say no.
And they'll do all the
VA paperwork for you.
We all know some of life's most
important financial
decisions are
made right here at
the kitchen table.
So, if you're a veteran
and need cash,
calling NewDay USA
could be one of
the best decisions
you'll ever make.
Go to NewDayUSA.com,
or call 1-877-42
>> DI, EVERYONE.
I'M DANA PERINO.
NEW REPON■■■N■N■N■N■IDEN W
JUMP IN THURSDAY.
ALL THIS BACK AND F
WAITING, DOES IT  IMAGE
QUESTION ON OUR
OWN BRET BAIER WILL WEIGH IBIDE■
AND KEVIN MCALEENAN JOINS ME TO
TALK ABOUT THE CRISIS OF THE
BOARD OF TRADE ONLY ON
"THE DAILY BRIEFING" ."
>> I BELIEVE WE NEED TO GET OUT
OF THIS PRESIDENT.
THAT'S WHY I'M RUNNING TO BECOME
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
BUT I BELIEVE WE ARE VERY GOOD
REASON TO BELIEVE THAT THERE IS
AN INVESTIGATION THAT HAS BEEN
CONDUCTED, WHICH HAS PRODUCED
EVIDENCE THAT TELLS US THIS
PRESIDENT AND HIS ADMINISTRATION
ENGAGED IN OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE.
I BELIEVE CONGRESS SHOULD TAKE
THE STEPS TOWARD IMPEACHMENT.
>> Melissa: KAMALA HARRIS
DEMOCRATS ADVOCATING FOR
IMPEACHMENT.
THIS, DESPITE SPEAKER PELOSI'S
ATTEMPT KDOWN THAT TALK
IN A CONFERENCE CALL WITH HER
CAUCUS YESTERDAY.
LET'S BRING IN OUR POWER PANEL,
DAN HENNINGER, DEPUTY EDITOR FOR
"THE WALL STREET JOURNAL"
EDITORh■pú■
PRIZE-WINNING AUTH
>> I THINK ESTABLISHING
HERSELF ALONG WITH
ELIZABETH WARREN IN TERMS OF THE
CANDIDATES THAT MOST WANT TO
HOLD THE PRESIDENT ACCOUNTABLE.
THAT MAY VERY WELL BE GOOD
POLITICS FOR THEM.
I'M NOT SURE IT'S GOOD POLITICS
FOR THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
IN FACT, IT'S PROBABLY
COUNTERPRODUCTIVE IF IT GOES
FORWARD.
RIGHT NOW I THINK NANCY PELOSI
HAS IT RIGHT.
LET THESE HEARINGS PLAY OUT, AND
LET THE AMERICAN PEOPLE BE
EDUCATED ABOUT WHAT'S IN THE
MUELLER REPORT.
LET'S FACE IT, MOST PEOPLE ARE
NOT GOING TO BE 440 PAGES.
AND NOW ONLY 6 OUT OF 10
DEMOCRATS WANT TO MOVE FORWARD
WITH IMPEACHMENT.
YOU HAVE AN EDUCATION PROCESS
THAT HAS TO TAKE PLACE BEFORE --
>> Melissa: SO THEY CAN
UNDERSTAND THEY SHOULD IMPEACH
HIM?
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
>> UNDERSTAND OF THE THINGS HE
WAS ACCUSED OF AND PART 22 OF
THE MUELLER REPORT -- THERE
WAS --
>> Melissa: YOU THINK THEY
QUALIFY FOR IMPEACHMENT?
>> I THINK THAT'S A THE PARTY
WILL HAVE TO MAKE BUT IT'S
CERTAINLY VERY SERIOUS, AND I
THINK IT'S SOMETHING THAT, BY
THE WAY, MUELLER THROUGH TO THE
CONGRESS.
>> JUDY, LET ME SAY, WITH
RESPECT -- THE QUICKNESS WITH
WHICH THIS STORY HAS PIVOTED
FROM THE RUSSIAN COLLUSION
NARRATIVE OF TWO YEARS ABOUT
WHICH THERE WAS NOTHING IN THE
MUELLER REPORT COME MUCH NOW WE
ARE ON THE IMPEACH TRUMPS
NARRATIVE OVER THE OBSTRUCTION
ISSUE.
THE COLLISION NARRATIVE HAS
EVAPORATED LIKE A SOAP BUBBLE
AND THE OBSTRUCTION IS FOR
OBSTRUCTING ACTS THAT NEVER
OCCURRED.
TRUMPET KNEW AT THE TIME THAT HE
HAD DONE NOTHING, RIGHT?
BY DEFINITION.
SINCE MUELLER CONCLUDED THERE IS
NOTHING TO THE COLLUSION
ACCUSATIONS.
THAT WE ARE IN THIS KIND OF
CONVERSATION ABOUT IMPEACHING
TRUMP FOR BAD BEHAVIOR INSIDE
THE WAREHOUSE.
>> Melissa: HE WAS BEING
FALSELY ACCUSED.
WHAT YOU THINK ABOUT THAT?
>> LOOK AT, IF YOU ARE
INSTRUCTING YOUR PEOPLE TO
SELECT THE CONGRESS AND
INSTRUCTING THEM TO LIE TO THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE, THAT IS VERY
SERIOUS.
TRYING TO A SYSTEM OF JUSTICE BY
GETTING PEOPLE FIRED IN YOUR
ADMINISTRATION, BAD FOR THE
COUNTRY.
>> WHY THE HEARINGS?
GO STRAIGHT TO IMPEACHMENT.
>> Melissa: THEN WHY IS HE
TRYING TO OR PREVENT JUSTICE IF
HE DIDN'T DO IT?
YOU SEE HOW IT KIND OF
UNDERMINES THE OBSTRUCTION
ARGUMENT?
IS NOT TRYING TO GET THEM TO
NOT ADMIT WHAT THEY HAD DONE,
BECAUSE THEY HADN'T DONE
>> THAT'S DIFFERENT THAN SAYING,
"GO OUT THERE AND TELL MY
STORY."
THAT'S DIFFERENT FROM SAYING,
"GO OUT THERE AND LIED TO THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
I WANT TO FIRE MUELLER.
THE ONLY REASON REALLY WASN'T
FIRED IS THAT DON BEGIN WITH DO
IT.
I THINK PEOPLE HAVE A RIGHT TO
KNOW THAT AND THEN THEY CAN MAKE
THEIR OWN DECISIONS ABOUT
WHETHER OR NOT THAT RISES TO THE
LEVEL OF --       DEL MIKE --
>> Melissa: WENT TO HAVE
WANTED TO FIRE MUELLER BECAUSE
HE KNEW HE WAS PURSUING
SOMETHING THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN?
THAT'S HOW I DEAL WITH THE
RUSSIAN COLLISION WASN'T REAL,
SO HE WAS LIKE, "WHY ARE WE
DOING THIS?"
>> CERTAINLY THE REASON HE WAS
DOING THESE THINGS IS BECAUSE
HE'S DONALD TRUMP.
HE KNEW HE HADN'T■ENYTHING
AND NOW HE'S REACHING AROUND AND
STRIKING OUT AT PEOPLE.
>> Melissa: WE'VE GOT TO GO.
MORE "OUTNUMBERED OVERTIME" IN
JUST A MINUTE.
♪ ♪
Drivers just wont put their
phones down.
We need a solution.
Introducing... Smartdogs.
The first dogs trained to train
humans.
Stopping drivers from: Liking.
Selfie-ing.
And whatever this is.
Available to the public...
never.
Smartdogs are not the answer.
But GEICO has a simple tip.
Turn on "Do Not Disturb While
Driving" mode.
Brought to you by GEICO.
♪ ♪
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH