Doif you aalo ILUMYA
or any of its ingredients.
Before starting treatment,
your doctor should check for
tuberculosis and infections.
After checking there is no need
for routine lab monitoring
unless your doctor advises it.
ILUMYA may increase your
risk of infections
and lower your ability
to fight them.
Tell your doctor if you have an
infection or have symptoms,
or if you plan to or have
recently received a vaccine.
This could be your chance
to leave your psoriasis
symptoms behind.
Ask your doctor ■átodarow.
So, you're open all day,
every day.
That's what 24/7 means, sugar.
Kind of like how you
get 24/7 access
to licensed agents with GEICO.
Hmm?
Yeah, you just go online,
or give them a call anytime.
You don't say.
Yep. Now what will it take
to get 24/7 access
to that lemon meringue pie?
PIE!
PIE'S COMING!
That's what it takes, baby.
GEICO®. Great service
from licensed agents, 24/7.
♪ ♪
There are roadside attractions.
And then there's our
world-famous
ON-road attraction.
If you've neen
yourself in a Mercedes, u'.
Lease the 2019 GLC 300
for just $479 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz
Spring Event.
Hurry in before April 30th.
00 PEECHP TURNS OUT SRI
LANKAN AUTHO@ RECEIVED ■@■@ ABOK
ABOUT THREE WEEKS AGO.
WHY WASN'T MORE DONE TO STOP
THIS?
FORMER U.S. MARINETA
COUNTERTERRORISM EXPERT JOINS US
NOW.
AIN, WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF
THIS, WHAT MANY ARE CALLING A
CREDIBLE ANDHE OF
COURSE THE TRAGEDY STILL PLAYING
OUT?
>> WHY THE SRI LANKAN
INTELLIGENCE SERVICES FAILED TO
ACT ON THE INFORMATION THEY HAD
AND WHY OFFICIALS INCLUDING THE
PRIME MINISTER WERE NOT ADVISED
OF THE INTELLIGENCE IS AN
ENORMOUS QUESTION AND AS YOU
INDICATED A POTENTIAL COLOSSAL
INTELLIGENCE FAILURE WHOSE
IMPACT IS MEASURED IN CLOSE TO
300 CASUALTIES AND OVER 500
WOUNDED.
>> Charles: COULD THEY HAVE
TAKEN TAKEN IT SERIOUSLY
CONSIDERING THE SMALL PERCENTAGE
OF SRI LANKANS WHO ARE
CHRISTIANS SLIGHTLY MORE ARE
MUSLIMS -- IT'S A 70% BUDDHIST
COUNTRY.
COULD THEY HAVE NOT THOUGHT THEY
WOULD BE A VIABLE TARGET FOR
THIS KIND OF THING?
>> I THINK THOSE ARE ALL FAIR
QUESTIONS AND PROBABLY AND
PRESUMABLY THE PURPOSE OF THE
COMMISSION THAT THE PRESIDENT
ANNOUNCED, OF COURSE, THAT
COMMISSION ITSELF HAS TO GET
THROUGH THE INFIGHTING THAT
EXISTS IN SRI LANKAN SOCIETY
WHICH I THINK IS PROBABLY IN
LARGE PART TO DO WITH THIS, THE
PRESIDENT, THE DEFENSE MINISTER
WHO CONTROLS SECURITY SERVICES
AND A PRIRS WHO WASN'T ABLE TO
CALL A NATIONAL SECURITY COUNCIL
MEETING, ALL THESE ARE LEADING
TO A BREAKDOWN IN COMMUNICATION
WHOSE CATASTROPHIC IMPACT WE SAW
ON EASTER SUNDAY.
>> Charles: WE KNOW THIS IS A
COUNTRY TASUFFERED THROUGH THEIR
OWN LONG-TERM -- THAT SUFFERED
THROUGH THEIR OWN LONG-TERM
CIVIL WAR, MUCH TALKED ABOUT THE
COMING TOGETHER AND REUNITING
AND LOOKING FORWARD.
IS THIS ONE OF THE REASONS ALSO
IT WAS SEEN AS AN EASY TARGET?
BECAUSE THE
MASTERMINDS BEHIND THIS WERE
ABLE TO PULL OFF REALLY AN
AMAZING CRIME AGAINST HUMANITY.
>> SRI LANKA HAS GENERALLY NOT
BEEN IMPACTED BY MUCH OF THE
SECTARIAN VIOLENCE WE'VE SEEN IN
OTHER PARTS OF SOUTHEAST ASIA AS
WELL AS INDIA AND PAKISTAN.
THIS GROUP ITSELF RELATIVELY
UNKNOWN THAT HAD NOT ARTICULATED
OR UNDERTAKEN A COMPLEX ATTACK
OR REALLY ANY ATTACK PRIOR.
IS GOING TO FORCE A LOT OF
QUESTIONS ABOUT WHATV WHAT'S
GOING ON AND I THINK WE'RE GOING
TO SEE BY THE NATURE OF THE
INTELLIGENCE THAT CAME THROUGH
FROM INTERNATIONAL INTELLIGENCE
SERVICES THAT THE SRI LANKANS
ALLEGEDLY HAD THAT SOME OF THEIR
STATEMENTS THAT THERE WAS A
LARGER NETWORK AT PLAY HERE WITH
INTERNATIONAL CONNECTIONS IS
GOING TO BEAR OUT.
>> Charles: WOULDN'T THIS SEEM
TO YOU WITH Y EXPERTISE THAT
THAT IS INDEED THE CASE?
SOME OF THE THINGS, A VAN BLOWN
UP THIS MORNING IN FRONT OF A
CHURCH.
IDEALLY THE BOVMINGS IN THE
CHURCH WOULD HAVE DRIVEN --
IDEALLY THE BOMBINGS IN THE
CHURCH WOULD HAVE DRIVEN
PARISHIONERS OUT AND THEY WOULD
HAVE BEEN DRIVEN INTO THE SECOND
BOMBING.
DOESN'T IT SEEM MORE THAN LIKELY
THAT THEY'VE HAD MAJOR OUTSIDE
HELP HERE?
>> I THINK THAT THAT IS CORRECT.
USUALLY WHEN YOU SEE THESE SORTS
OF COMPLEX, COORDINATED ATTACKS
IT REQUIRES A LOT OF FUNDING.
A LOT OF PLANNING.
THE GROUP HAD NOT DEMONSTRATED
THAT IN THE PAST.
ALSO, THE SHEER SUCCESS, THE
COMPLEXITY OF THE DEVICES THAT
WERE USED USUALLY REQUIRES
GROUPS THAT ARE OPERATING
INDEPENDENTLY OR WITH SINGLE
INDIVIDUALS, A NUMBER OF
ATTEMPTS.
THIS GROUP PULLED IT OFF WITH AT
LEAST EIGHT COORDINATED
DETONATIONS AS WELL AS ANOTHER
DEVICE THAT WAS DEFUSED THAT WE
KNOW OF AT THIS TIME.
THAT'S INDICATIVE OF A MUCH
LARGER, BROADER PLOT AND ALSO
INDIVIDUALS INVOLVED.
AND I THINK THE FACT THAT THE
AVAILABLE ALSO INDICATES THAT.
>> CharlesAS AN ATTACK
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN A CONDO
LAST WEEK BY ISIS TOO.
WHY THEY BEEN CRUSHED SO BADLY
IN THE MILITARY THEATERS THAT
THEY'RE GOING TO PLACES WE
HAVEN'T SEEN THEM BEFORE?
>> WE HAVE SEEN ATTACKS ACROSS
AFRICA.
ACROSS SOUTHEAST ASIA.
I THINK THIS IS THE NEW NORMAL
AS WE DECIMATED THEIR ABILITY TO
OPERATE IN IRAQ AND SYRIA, THEY
ARE LOOKING TO OTHER LOCATIONS
HERE AT HOME AS WELL. AT.
>> Charles: MICHAEL MASTERS,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE IT.
30 MINUTES FROM A BIG CONFERENCE
CALL WITH HOUSE DEMOCRATS ON THE
MUELLER REPORT.
SEVERAL MEMBERS WILL BE PUSHING
FOR IMPEACHMENT OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
HE'S PUSHING BACK.
NEXT.
j÷
It's Cedar Plank Seafood time
at Red Lobster!
Featuring three new dishes that
are planked-to-perfection.
Feast on NEWlank
Lobster & Shrimp.
Or NEW Colossal Shrimp & Salmon
with a citrusy drizzle.
Tender, smoky, and together
on one plank...
...but not for long-
so hurry in!
(ding)
Hey, who are you?
Oh, hey Jeff, I'm a car thief...
What?!
I'm here to
steal your car because,
well, that's my job.
What?
What??
WHAT?!
(laughing)
What??
WHAT?!
What?!
[crash]
WHAT?!
Haha, it happens.
And if you've got
cut-rate car insurance,
paying for this could
feel like getting robbed twice.
So get Allstate...
and be better protected
from MKK me.
♪
Travel and dining
just g
Now KAYAK and OpenTable
let you earn travel rewards
every time you dine.
Earn points with each restaurant
reservation on OpenTable
and redeem them for
hotel discounts on KAYAK.
Get started at
KAYAK.com/diningrewards.
Hey whoa, pop, pop...
your shoe's untied.
♪ ♪
Ensure he's well taken care of,
even as you build your own plans
for retirement.
See how Lincoln can help.
>> Charles: SHARES OF TESLA
SHORT-CIRCUITING TODAY,
4%.
THE ELECTRIC CAR COMPANY
INVESTIGATING AN APPARENT
EXPLOSION OF AD DEL-S
R IN SHANGHAI.
This is Huntsville, Alabama.
AKA, Rocket City, USA.
This is a very difficult job.
Failure is not an option.
More than half of employees
across the country
bring financial stress to work.
If you're stressed out
financially at home,
you're going to be too worried
to be able to do a good job.
I want to be able to offer all
of the benefits
that keep them satisfied.
It is the people that is really
the only asset that you have.
Put your employees on a path
to financial wellness
with Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
Does this map show the
Peninsula Trail?
You won't find that on a map.
I'll take you there.
Take this left.
If you listen real hard you can
hear the whales.
Oop.
You hear that?
(VO) Our Subaru Outback
lets us see the world.
Sometimes in ways
we never imagined.
>> Charles: HOUSE SPEAKER NANCY
PELOSI IS HOLD A
CONFERENCE CALL WITH HOUSE
DEMOCRATS MOMENTS FROM ON
TO RO THE MUELLER
REPORT.
AT LEAST THREEEMOCRATS ARE
PUSHIN■ IMPEACHMENT BUT THE
PRESIDENT DOESN'T APPEAR TOO
CONCERNED.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT■
IMPEACHMENT, MR. PRESIDENT?
>> NOT EVEN A LITTLE BIT.
>> Charles: PRESIDENT TRUMP
SAYING HE'S NOT WORRIED.
NOT EVEN A LITTLE BIT.
HOW IS THIS ALL GOING TO PLAY
OUT POLITICALLY?
LET'S ASK G.O.P. STRATEGIST,
DEMOCRAT STRATEGIST AND ""THE
DAILY MAIL"'S" FRANCESCA.
THERE IS ANXIETY ON THE
DEMOCRATIC SIDE.
OLDER FOLKS, STE HOYER'S AND
EVEN COREY BOOKER■■@/@/@/@/@/@/7
@/@/TH■7@/@/@/@/@/@/CHARLES.
THAT'S WHY@/@/@/@/@/@/@/@/@/@/I7
■7@/@/@7@7@7@7■7■7■7@7■7■7@/@/@
THE MUPO
IT'S IMPORTANT TO REMIND@7 THAT
CONGRESS I OF SESSION THIS
WEEK WHY THEY ARE HAVING THEIR@7
@7@7@7 LUNCHEON AND
HAVING THIS CONFERENCE CALL AT
5:00 P.M. AND NANCY PELOSI AHEAD
OF THAT A LETTER TO@/
COLLEAGUES NOTING THAT S
FOR I@/@/@/@/@/@/@/@/■7@/@/@/@/
NOT.
DEMOCRATS CLEARLY SPLIT ON WHAT
TO DO NEXT, PARTICULARLY AS THEY
HEAD INTO 2020.
>> Charles: ELIZABETH WARREN IS
FOR IMPEACHMENT.
OCASIO-CORTEZ, RASHEED TLAIB.
SOME OF THE MORE OUTSPOKEN
MEMBERS.
>> IT'S NOT SPLIT 50-50, IT'S
SPLIT ABOUT 90-10 AGAINST THE
IDEA OF IMPEACHMENT.
IMPEACHMENT IS NOT A SERIOUS
PROPOSAL.
YOU HAVE A REPUBLICAN SENATE
WHICH WILL NEVER VOTE TO REMOVE
THE PRESIDENT.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE ENO VOTES
IN THE HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES
TO HAVE IMPEACHMENT APPROVED
EVEN ALONG A PURE PARTY-LINE
VOTE.
WE HAVE RED-STATE DEMS ON THE
BALLOT IN 2020 WHO NEED MODERATE
POSITIONS IN ORDER TO WIN SO
UNLESS WE WANT TO HAVE A PARTY
THAT IS ONLY A.O.C., THAT IS
ONLY ELIZABETH WARREN THAT IS A
FRINGE POLITICAL MOVEMENT WHILE
THE 2K3W07 G.O.P. DOMINATES THE
REST OF THE COUNTRY THIS HAS TO
BE TAKEN OFF THE TABLE AND
CONCENTRATE ON THINGS MIDDLE
CLASS VOTERS WANT.
>> Charles: BY THE SAME TOKEN
YOU HAVE A TON OF INVESTIGATION,
YOU HAVE ELIJAH CUMMINGS ASKING
FOR INFORMATION, VUJERRY NADLER
IN NEW YORK.
THERE ARE DEMOCRATS CONTINUINGS
CONTINUING TO PUSH THE ISSUE
POST MUELLER REPORT AND SOME
THINK THIS COULD BE A MAJOR
MISTAKE.
>> IT WILL BE A HUGE MISTAKE AND
THERE IS A HUGE DEMAND FOR BLUE
MEAT IN THE DEMOCRATIC BASE.
IN THE PRESIDENTIAL PRIMARY
THERE IS GOING TO BE A RUSH TO
THE LEFT TO SEE WHO CAN TAKE THE
MOST EXTREME POSITION BECAUSE
IT'S GOING TO PLAY WELL WITH THE
VOTERS AND THE SENIOR
ESTABLISHMENT OF THE DEMOCRATS
KNOW THAT IT'S GOING TO BACKFIRE
SO THEY'RE TRYING TO WALK IT
BACK BUT THE MEDIA IS GOING TO
KEEP STOKING IT AND THE
DEMOCRATS WHO WANT TO MAKE A
NAME FOR THEMSELVES ARE GOING TO
KEEP TALKING ABOUT IT BUT IT'S
NOT A SERIOUS PROPOSAL AND THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE WANT NOTHING TO
DO WITH IT.
>> Charles: ON THE OTHER SIDE,
THE HOUSE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE'S
RANK MEMBER JIM JORDAN TELLING
NEIL CAVUTO ON "CAVUTO LIVE" HE
WANTS TO GET TO THE BOTTOM OF
THE RUSSIA PROBE.
>> PEOPLE ARE TIRED OF THIS
DOUBLE STANCE.
THIS IDEA THERE IS ONE SET OF
RULES FOR REGULAR PEOPLE BUT A
DIFFERENT SET IF YOUR IDEA IS
COMEY, LYNCH OR LERNER, THEY
WANT PEOPLE TO LAUNCH THESE
INVESTIGATIONS ON THE FALSE
PREMISE.
THEY DO WANT THEM HELD
ACCOUNTABLE AND I THINK IT'S
IMPORTANT WE GET TO THE BOTTOM
OF THIS BECAUSE AS I SAID THAT
IS NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HOW IT
WORKS IN THIS COUNTRY.
>> Charles: FRANCESCA, A DOUBLE
STANDARD HERE?
>> REPUBLICANS ALSO HAVE TO
HALF INVESTIGATING THE T TO SPE/
MEANWHILE,RATS OR IF T@/@/ PHE /
TO CHOOSE WHETHER THEY W TO
GO FOR AGENDA ITEMS THAT THEY@/
RANO IN 2018 OR THEY WOULD LIKE
TO INVESHEENT.
L CHOOSE TOEEP PUSHINGT
THAT THEYL@/
NOT GO A■/■/ @/
THEY THIS■/ LOSING ISSUE
FOR D IN 20
SARAH SANDERS SAYING THEY SHOULD
EADY LEARNED THAT THIS
ISN'T A WINNING MESSAGE FOR THEM
AND THAT THEY WON'T BE ABLE TO
BEAT PRESIDENT TRUMP ON IT IN
2020.
>> Charles: ROBERT, DO YOU THINK
THERE IS AN EQUIVALENCE ISSUE
THEUBLICANS SAYING SINCE WE
SPENT SO MUCH TIME AND MONEY
ANXIETY OVER THIS MUELLER REPORT
GET TO THE BOTTOM OF IT, TO
QUOTE PRESIDENT TRUMP NO OTHER
PRESIDENT HAS TO GO THROUGH THIS
AGAIN?
>> LET'S UNDERSTAND HOW DUMB AN
IDEA THIS IS FOR REPRESENTATIVE
JORDAN.
LET'S TAKE THE PRESIDENT AT HIS
WORD THAT HE SAYS HE WAS
COMPLETELY EXONERATED BY THE
MUELLER REPORT.
NO COLLUSION.
NO OBSTRUCTION.
BY REOPENING THIS CAN OF WORMS
TO INVESTIGATE THE
INVESTIGATORS, THAT'S GOING TO
BRING ALL THESE THINGS BACK INTO
THE PUBLIC EYE.
THAT'S GOING TO HAVE MORE
INVESTIGATIONS.
HAVE MORE HOUSE SUBPOENAS ON
TRUMP PRESIDENTIAL RECORDS.
THEY'RE GOING TO BE REOPENING
TAKING THIS BANDAGE OFF A WOUND
THAT MIGHT END UP HURTING THE
PRESIDENT IN THE LONG RUN.
>> Charles: SOME SAY THERE WAS
NEVER AN INVESTIGATION OF THE
ORIGINS OF THE FISA REPORT AND
SOME OF THE OTHER THINGS THAT
WERE NEFARRIOUS FROM THE START
AND SHOULD HAVE BEEN FLAGGED AS
NEFARIOUS FROM THE START.
>> THERE IS NO STANDARD AT ALL.
THERE IS NO PRECEDENT FOR
INVESTIGATING WHAT WAS A RUSSIAN
HACK AND IT SPIRALLED INTO
SOMETHING COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
AND METASTASIZED INTO
INVESTIGATING THE PRESIDENT AND
EVERYBODY IN HIS ORBIT FOR
COLLUSION THAT HE DIDN'T COMMIT
AND THAT NEVER HAPPENED.
THIS IS AN EXERCISE IN PROPER
GOVERNANCE TO ENSURE THAT THIS
DOESN'T HAPPEN TO ANOTHER
PRESIDENT.
>> Charles: THANK YOU ALL VERY
MUCH.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
MEANWHILE, THE F.B.I. ARRESTING
THE LEADER OF AN ARMED MILITIA
GROUP POLICING THE NEW MEXICO
SOUTHERN BORDER OVER THE WEEKEND
WITH CITIZENS TAKING THE LAW
INTO THEIR OWN HANDS.
WHAT DOES THIS IS A ABOUT THE
CURRENT MIGRANT CRISIS?
What do you charge for
online equity trades?
Uh, I'll look into it.
(Phone rings)
Lisa Jones!
Lisa: (On phone) Hey Carl,
what are you charging me
for online equity trades?
(Nervous chuckle)
Lisa:
And do I get my fees back
if I'm not happy?
Like a Satisfaction Guarantee?
Ugh. Schwab!
Lisa:
Oh right, I'm calling Schwab.
Thanks, Carl!
Wait, Lisa! Lisa...
Are you getting low costs
backed by
a satisfaction guarantee?
If not, talk to Schwab.
A modern approach to wealth
management.
>> Charles: LARRY  THE
LEADER OF AN■RMEDROUPINING UNDO
IN NEW MEXICO AFTER C THE
ER N■G FEDERAL
CHARGES.
IS BORDER PATROL SO OVERWHELMED
THAT ORDINARY CITIZENS FEEL THE
NEED TO STEP IN?
CARL LANDRUM JOINS ME NOW TO
DISCUSS.
FIRST, CITIZENS THERE TAKING UP
ARMS, TRYING TO ASSIST.
WHAT WOULD YOU TELLTHEM?
IT'S APPARENT TO THE THAT
WE'VE GOT A CRISIS DOWN THERE
AND THEY'RE TRYING TO HELP OUT.
>> FIRST OF ALL, THANKS FOR
HAVING ME, CHAR
WHEN IT COMES TO CITIZENS TRYING
TO HELP US OOWN ON THE
BORDER LIKE THIS, THEY NEED TO
REMEMBER THAT CUSTOMS AND BORDER
PROTECTION DOES NOT ENDORSE THIS
TYPE OF ACTIVITY BY ANY PRIVATE
GROUP OR ORGANIZATION.
ON THE BORDER.
THE BORDER ENVIRONMENT IS A VERY
COMPLEX ENVIRONMENT AND IT DOES
REQUIRE VERY UNIQUE SKILL SETS
TO BE ABLE TO OPERATE SAFELY AND
EFFICIENTLY DOWN IN THAT AREA,
AND ALL OF OUR BORDER PATROL
AGENTS THAT WORK THERE AS WELL
AS OTHER AGENCIES, AGENTS AND
OFFICERS THAT WORK IN THE AREA
ARE HIGHLY TRAINED AND BRING
IQUE SKILL SETS TO THAT
NMENT.
>> Charles: SO "THANKS BUT NO
THANKS, PLEASE."
YUMA DECLARED AN EMERGENCY.
THE NUMBERS MASSIVE THROUGHOUT
THE SOUTHERN BORDER BUT YUMA
STANDING OUT MORE RECENTLY.
WHAT CAN BE DONE?
BECAUSE WE DO SEE THE CRISIS.
WE SEE SEVERAL CARAVANS FORMING.
NONSTOP.
WHAT IS THE NEAR-TERM SOLUTION?
WHAT CAN HELP WITH THE SITUATION
NOW?
>> IT IS AN ABSOLUTE CRISIS FOR
US, IN YUMA AS WELL AS OTHER
PLACES ACROSS THE SOUTHWEST
BORDER OF THE UNITED STATES.
YUMA IS -- THE AMOUNT OF
ACTIVITY, ILLEGAL ENTRIES
OCCURRING THERE ARE GROWING
LITERALLY MONTH BY MONTH
AVERAGING ABOUT 300 A DAY IN
YUMA AND THE PROBLEM THERE IS
THAT THE CAPACITY THAT WE HAVE
TO DEAL WITH THE SITUATION, TO
TAKE THESE PEOPLE INTO CUSTODY
AND PROCESS THEM IN ACCORDANCE
WITH OUR GUIDANCE IS JUST
OVERWHELMED.
>> Charles: HOW MANY CAN YOU
NORMALLY HANDLE ON A TYPICAL DAY
WITH THE MANPOWER THAT YOU
CURRENTLY HAVE?
>> OUR CAPACITY IN YUMA IS ABOUT
410 PEOPLE.
THAT'S NORMALLY WHAT WE CAN HOLD
AND WE'RE DESIGNED TO HOLD
SINGLE ADULTS FOR UP TO 12
HOURS.
>> Charles: SO 300 A DAY AND
YOU'RE ONLY EQUIPPED TO HOLD
400.
OBVIOUSLY OVERWHELMED.
HOW COME IT WAS -- IT S
LIKE WHOEVER IS COMING HAS
NCE KNOWLEDGE OF THIS
SITUATION.
HOW ARE THEY LEARNING THIS?
HOW ORGANIZED IS THIS?
BECAUSE IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE
BEING OVERWHELMED BUT IT'S A
DELIBERATE ACTION.
>> THE MOCHT OF THESE PEOPLE
THROUGHOUT THE WESTERN --
>> THE MOVEMENT OF THESE PEOPLE
THROUGHOUT THE WESTERN
HEMISPHERE IS TRIGGERED BY
TRANSNATIONAL CRIMINAL
ORGANIZATIONS PROFITING FROM THE
MOVEMENT OF THESE HUMAN BEINGS
THROUGHOUT THE WESTERN
HEMISPHERE AND INTO THE UNITED
STATES.
>> Charles: CARL, WE'VE HAD THIS
DISCUSSION.
IT'S OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
THE CRISIS CONTINUES TO GET WORK
ON A DAILY BASIS.
WE HEAR CONSTANTLY.
IT'S CONGRESS THAT HAS TO
RESOLVETHIS.
FOR THE MEN AND WOMEN DOING YOUR
JOB, IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE TO
GIVE SHORT-TERM RELIEF?
>> IMMEDIATELY HELPING US
INCREASE CAPACITY.
THAT WOULD HELP IN THE IMMEDIATE
NEAR TERM BUT LONG-TERM LIKE YOU
MENTIONED WE DO NEED THE SUPPORT
OF CONGRESS AND THE SUPPORT OF
EVERY AMERICAN IN THE UNITED
STATES TO GET WHAT WE NEED IN
ORDER TO SECURE THE BORDER OF
THE UNITED STATES.
>> Charles: IF THESE FOLKS WERE
ALLOWED TO REQUEST ASYLUM IN
THEI COUNTRIES, WOULD THAT
HELP THE SITUATION AT ALL?
>> THAT WOULD HELP THE SITUATION
BUT AS AN EXAMPLE, IN YUMA
SPECIFICALLY WHERE I WORK, IN
THAT PARTICULAR AREA, ONLY 6% OF
THE PEOPLE CROSSING THE BORDER
ARE EXPRESSING A CREDIBLE FEAR
AND REQUESTING ASYLUM SO WE
WOULD STILL HAVE AN ISSUE WITH
THE INABILITY TO DETAIN A FAMILY
UNIT, ESPECIALLY WITH A CHILD,
FOR GREATER THAN 20 DAYS.
>> Charles: WE THANK YOU FOR
YOUR JOB.
WE UNDERSTAND HOW TOUGH IT IS.
WE APPRECIATE YOU COMING ON.
>> THANKS, CHARLES.
>> Charles: NEW LEGAL BATTLE
HEATING UP WITH PRESIDENT TRUMP
FILING A SUIT TO BLOCK A
SUBPOENA OF HIS FINANCIAL
RECORDS.
DOES HE HAVE A CASE?
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
Every day, visionaries are
creating the future.
So, every day,
we put our latest technology
and unrivaled network to work.
The United States Postal
Service makes more
e-commerce deliveries
to homes
than anyone else
in the country.
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
e-commerce deliveries
to homes
What do all these people
have in common, LiMu?
[ guttural grunt ]
Exactly. Nothing!
They're completely
different people.
That's why they
make customized
car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need.
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done it again, LiMu.
[ LiMu grunts ]
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
>> Charles: PRESIDENT TRUMP
SUING HOUSE OVERSIGH@ COMMITTEE
CHAIRMAN ELIJAH CUMMINGS IN A
BID TO BLOCK A SUBPOENA SEEKING
INFORMATION ON HIS FINANCES.
WHO HAS THE LEGAL HIGH GROUND?
TRIAL ATTORNEY LISAKOHARSKI
JOINS US.
LISA, THIS IS SUCH A FASCINATING
CASE.
WALK US THROUGH THIS
COUNTERATTACK OR
COUNTERPUNCH-BACK BY PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
>> SURE.
HE MADE A MOTION TO QUASH THE
SUBPOENA.
THERE ARE ESSENTIALLY TWO
SUBPOENAS.
WE HAVE ONE FROM THE OVERSIGHT
COMMITTEE.
WE HAVE ONE FROM WAYS AND MEANS■
COMMITTEE. #■
THIS MOTION IS TO QUASH THE OVE
AGAINST ELIJAH CUMMINGS AND HE
COULD POSSIBLY BE SUCCESSFUL.
THEY ARE LOOKING FOR A
SUBSTANTIAL AMOUNT OF
INFORMATION NOT ONLY FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP HIMSELF BUT ALSO
FROM A LOT OF ASSOCIATES.
>> Charles: IS THERE PRECEDENT
FOR THIS?
IT SEEMS SO UNIQUE THAT HE COULD
POSSIBLY BE SUCCESSFUL.
BASED ON WHAT?
>> YOU HAVE TO LOOK AT EVERY
CASE INDIVIDUALLY BUT WHEN A
COMMITTEE ASKS FOR THIS TYPE OF
INFORMATION, WHEN THEY SUBPOENA
INFORMATION OR THEY WANT TO
ENGAGE IN PERFORMING
INVESTIGATIONS, THE CONSTITUTION
STILL IS IN EFFECT AND THE
CONSTITUTION STATES THEY NEED A
LEGITIMATE LEGISLATIVE PURPOSE,
SO IN THE FIRST SUBPOENA WE
DON'T SEE THAT.
THE SUBPOENA THAT CAME FROM
OVERSIGHT.
THEY ASKED FOR A LOT OF
INFORMATION.
THEY SUBPOENAED THE ACCOUNTANTS.
ALL HIS CORPORATIONS.
ASKING FOR INFORMATION PREDATIN
>> Charles: IT'S A FISHING
EXPEDITION.
>> IN A LOT OF WAYS IT IS, YES,
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR SOMETHING
AND OBVIOUSLY I THINK THE
AMERICAN PUBLIC IS GETTING QUITE
WEARY FOR THIS FISHING
EXPEDITION ESPECIALLY FOLLOWING
THE MUELLER REPORT.
WEANT TO SEE OUR LEGISLATORS
GOVERNb b ■ ■ ■ ■ b ■ ■ ■ ■ b b■
IN THIS CASE■ A VERY NARROW
ASK.
IN THE SECOND SUBPOENA THEY DID
COME UP WITH AIMATE
PURPOSE SO WE HAVE
REPRES■8 NOW S■8 WE
INTERESTING IT'S@■LI KIND OF EF
CART -- CARTEFORE THE■
>> C IT■■■ SEEMS A LITTLE
SPECIOUS AND CONFUSING AT THE
VERY LEAST.
WITH THIS COUNTERSUIT OR
PUSH-BACK FROM PRESIDENT TRUMP
HE DID IT AS SORT OF CITIZEN
TRUMP NOT PRESIDENT TRUMP AND I
THOUGHT THAT INTERESTING.
WHY WOULD HE DO THAT?
>> I THINK THEY'RE TRYING TO
MAKE A DELINEATION BETWEEN THE
FACT THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP, A LOT
OF THE INFORMATION THAT WAS
REQUESTED AND SUBPOENAED WAS
REQUESTED OF CITIZEN TRUCH.
HE WAS NOT THE ACTING PRESIDENT.
HE WAS NOT ELECTED TO OFFICE.
THEY'RE ASKING THIRD PARTIES
INVOLVED IN ALL OF HIS ANCILLARY
BUSINESSES -- WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT 10'S OF THOUSANDS OF PAGES
OF DOCUMENTS AND TAX RETURNS
THAT ARE GOING TO BE SUBPOENAED
TO PEOPLE THAT QUITE FRANKLY
MANY OF THEM PROBABLY AREN'T
EQUIPPED TO EVEN LOOK INTO THESE
TAX RETURNS.
>> Charles: SOME OF THE NAMES.
ALL THE MEMBERS OF HIS FAMILY.
EVEN HIS SON BARON.
HOW DOES THAT WORK?
IT SEEMS SO -- SUCH AN
OVERREACH.
>> WHEN YOU CAST YOUR LINE, YOU
WANT TO CAST IT INTO A SCHOOL OF
FISH HOPING TO GET SOMETHING AND
THAT'S KIND OF WHAT WE'RE
SEEING.
IN REALITY WHAT IS THE ULTIMATE
OUTCOME?
I THINK EVERY AMERICAN IS ASKING
THIS QUESTION AND THE REAL THING
IS EVEN IF THEY WERE TO FIND
SOME■ILING A■■ TAX■■#RETURN COU
MISDEMEANOR, HIGH KRIEPZ AND --
HIGH CRIMES AND MISDEMEANORS.
>> Charles: THAT'S NOT WHAT
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR.
WE HAD A TWO-YEAR MUELLER
REPORT, THE MEDIA SAID THIS WAS
THE BEST GUY FOR THE JOB, THE
DEMOCRATS RAISED ROBERT LER,
THEY DIDN'T LIKE WHAT THEY GOT
SO THIS FISHING EXPEDITION WHICH
YOU'RE SAYING ANYTHING THEY FIND
IN HERE COULD BE LEVERAGED AND
CONSIDERED NOW THE PLATFORM TO
GO AFTER SOME ADDITIONAL --
>> CERTAINLY.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHY YOU REQUEST
THE INFORMATION BUT AGAIN, YOU
HAVE TO LOOK AT WHERE THIS
INVESTIGATION IS GOING AND THE
--
>> Charles: YOU THINK PRESIDENT
TRUMP HAS A GOOD CASE TO PUSH
BACK?
>> I THINK HE HAS A GOOD CASE.
EVEN IF HE DIDN'T HAVE A GOOD
CASE, ONCE IT'S IN THE DISTRICT
COURT AND IT'S APPEALED IT WILL
GO UP TO THE SUPREME COURT AND
CERTAINLY THE MOTIVES BEHIND IT
-- IF THERE IS A POLITICAL
MOTIVE THE SUPREME COURT WILL
QUASH THE SUBPOENA AND WE'LL
ALREADY HAVE A NEW PRESIDENT.
>> Charles: A POLITICAL MOTIVE
BEHIND TDENT EVEN WALK
INTO A COURTROOM WOULD BE
CONSIDERED A VICTORY.
LISA, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WE'RE MINUTES AWAY FROM
DEMOCRATS AND THEIR NEXT MOVE ON
THE MUELLER REPORT AND
IMPEACHMENT.
WE'VE GOT THE LATEST ON ALL THAT
NEXT.
■■■■
I've always been amazed
by what's next.
And still going for my best,
even though I live with
a higher risk of stroke
due to Afib not caused by
a heart valve problem.
So if there's a better treatment
than warfarin...
I want that too.
ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS is proven
to reduce stroke risk
better than warfarin.
Plus has significantly less
major bleeding than warfarin.
ELIQUIS is FDA-approved
and has both.
What's next?
Reeling in a nice one.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS
unless your doctor tells you to,
as stopping increases your risk
of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS If you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily
and it may take longer than
usual for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden sign of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase your
bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor
about all planned medical
or dental procedures.
ELIQUIS, the number one
cardiologist-prescribed
blood thinner.
Ask your doctor
if ELIQUIS
Don't tell your mother.
is what's next
for you.
Dad, it's fine.
We have ALLSTATE.
AND WITH CLAIMRATEGUARD
THEY WON'T RAISE YOUR RATES
JUST BECAUSE OF A CLAIM.
That's why you're my favorite...
I KNOW.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
>> Charles: HOUSE SPEAKER
NANCY PELOSI SAID A CONFERENCE
CALL WITH DEMOCRATS TO DISCUSS
THE ROLLER REPORT.
PETER DOOCY IS IN D.C. WITH THE
LATEST.
>> HOUSE DEMOCRATS THAILAND FOR
A CONFERENCE CALL THAT STARTS
INTO AN A HALF MINUTES AND THE
PRIMER THEY GOT FROM
NANCY PELOSI WAS A LETTER WAVING
THEM AWAY FROM IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDINGS.
SHE WRITES IN PART "WHILE OUR
VIEWS RANGE FROM PROCEEDING TO
INVESTIGATE THE FINDINGS OF THE
MUELLER REPORT OR PROCEEDING
DIRECTLY TO IMPEACHMENT, WE ALL
FIRMLY AGREE WE SHOULD PROCEED
DOWN THE PATH OF FINDING THE
TRUTH AND IT'S ALSO IMPORTANT TO
KNOW THAT THE FACTS REGARDING
HOLDING THE PRESIDENT
ACCOUNTABLE CAN BE GAINED
OUTSIDE OF IMPEACHMENT
HEARINGS."
THAT STATEMENT SEEMS TO CONFLICT
WITH PRIORITIES LAID OUT BY THE
TOP DEMOCRAT ON THE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE, JERRY NADLER.
>> DO YOU THINK THIS IS
IMPEACHABLE?
>> YEAH, I DO.
I DO THINK IF PROVEN, IF PROVEN,
WHICH HASN'T BEEN PROVEN YET, IF
PROVEN, SOME OF THIS WOULD BE
IMPEACHABLE, YES.
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE, IF
PROVEN, WOULD BE IMPEACHABLE."
>>  SPEAK OF PRESIDENT WEIGHED ,
TWEETING:
"ONLY HIGH CRIMES AND
MISDEMEANORS CAN LEAD TO
IMPEACHMENT.
THERE WERE NO CRIMES BY ME
NO COLLUSION, NO OBSTRUCTION,
SO YOU CAN'T IMPEACH.
IT WAS THE DEMOCRATS THAT
COMMITTED THE CRIMES, NOT YOUR
REPUBLICAN PRESIDENT!
TABLES ARE FINALLY TURNING
ON THE WITCH HUNT!"
TODAY OF THE EASTERN ROLE,
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS ASKED IF HE
IS WORRIED ABOUT IMPEACHMENT AND
HE SAID NOT EVEN A LITTLE BIT.
CHARLES.
>> Charles: PETER, SO EVERYONE
IS A LITTLE ANXIOUS ON HOW
NANCY PELOSI HANDLES THE MORE
THAT'S THE REAL CGE ONY ON THIS.
THIS CALL, ISN'T IT?
>> THERE ARE GOING TO BE DOZENS
OF PEOPLE ON THIS CALL.
THEY HAVE BEEN ON RECENT SUITS
THE DETAILS OF THE MUELLER
REPORT WERE PROBABLY RELEASED
AND NANCY PELOSI WAS OUT OF THE
COUNTRY LAST WEEK SO THIS IS THE
FIRST CHANCE FOR HUNDREDS OF
PEOPLE ALL TO ALL DAY ALONE AND
HEAR WHAT SHE HAS TO SAY AND
THEN POTENTIALLY BE HEARD.
OF CHARLES.
>> Charles: I CAN'T WAIT.
WE WILL GET THE POPCORN.
THANKS.
APPRECIATE IT.
LISTEN, TODAY WAS AN INTERESTING
DAM AND MARKETS, THE DOW CAME
BACK BUT IT STILL FINISH LOWER.
THE OTHER MAJOR INDICES, THE S&P
AND NASDAQ WERE HIGHER.
WE HAVE SOME MAJOR EARNINGS OUT
THIS WEEK AND THIS WILL BE AN
EVENTFUL WEEK.
DON'T FORGET THE MARKETS, ALL
THREE MAJOR INDICES ABOUT 1.5
PERCENTAGE POINTS AWAY FROM
ALL-TIME HIGHS THANKS FOR
JOINING US.
NEIL WILL BE BACK TOMORROW.