FAMILY.
OBVIOUSLY EMOTION.
I WANT TO CHOKE THAT'S ON
ABOUT...
I THINK BERNIE IS BEING SINCERE
HERE AND I TELL YOU WHY.
IF YOU LOOK AT PEOPLE WHO BEEN
IN PRISON, THERE IS A SENTIMENT
AND I THINK IT CROSSES CLINICAL
PARTIES THAT SAYS THOSE PEOPLE
HAVE TO BE REENTERED INTO
SOCIETY.
>> Greg: I AM ONE OF THOSE
PEOPLE.
>> Juan: OKAY.
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT HOUSING AND
JOBS, IF YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
WELFARE, YOU SAY THAT GUY
COMMITTED A FELONY.
HE CAN'T REENTER SOCIETY.
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT IS
GOING TO BE A HIGH LEVEL OF
PEOPLE GOING BACK TO CRIME.
>> Greg: YOU ARE A TERRIBLE
THERAPIST.
I CAME TO YOU WITH THE PROBLEM
AND YOU SOLVED -- YOU ARE GOING,
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS OTHER
PROBLEM.
I HAVE NIGHT TERRORS.
JESSE, WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THIS?
KEEPT SEPARATE, WHAT'S HIS
WHAT'S HIS NAME AGAIN?
BERNIE.
HE'S TALKING ABOUT PEOPLE IN
JAIL, TERRORISTS.
>> Jesse: DEMOCRATS WANT
TERRORISTS TO VOTE.
THINK ABOUT THAT, GREG.
THEY JUST HANDLED DONALD TRUMP
THE WEDGE USED OF WEDGE ISSUES.
JUAN, I HAVE A QUESTION.
ARE DEMOCRATS TRYING TO LOSE THE
ELECTION.
MADE TO ORDER FOR DONALD TRUMP.
THIS IS WILLIE HORTON 2.0.
>> Juan: YOU THINK WILLIE
HORTON IS GOOD NEWS?
OKAY.
>> Jesse: THIS IS WHAT IT'S
LIKE.
THEY HAVE TOTALLY UNDERCUT THEIR
WHOLE MESSAGING ON ELECTION
INTEGRITY.
THEY HAVE BEEN SAYING THE
RUSSIANS HAVE BEEN TRYING TO
HACK THE DEMOCRACY.
THEN THEY WANT TO SET UP VOTING
BOOTHS ON DEATH ROW.
I WONDER IF THERE'S EVER GOING
TO BE ANY CORRUPTION OR FRAUD
WITH THE VOTING PROCESS IN
PRISON WHEN YOU HAVE GUARDS WITH
BATONS LOOKING DOWN ON GUYS
FILLING OUT THEIR BALLOTS.
IT'S THE MOST RIDICULOUS THING
I'VE EVER SEEN AND THE REASON
THEY ARE DOING THIS, JUAN, IS
BECAUSE THEY CAN'T PERSUADE
ENOUGH ACTUAL VOTERS ABOUT THEIR
IDEAS SO THEY HAVE TO CREATE NEW
VOTERS.
THEY GOT ROCKED IN 2016, SO
INSTEAD OF TRYING TO CHANGE
THEIR MESSAGE, THEY ARE JUST
TRYING TO CHANGE THE RULES.
THIS IS WHAT THEY DID WITH THE
SUPREME COURT EXPANSION.
THIS IS THE ELECTORAL COLLEGE
ALL OVER AGAIN.
DO YOU THINK PEDOPHILES VOTING
OR SERIAL RAPISTS VOTING IS
GOING TO PLAY IN IOWA?
DEMOCRATS ARE TRYING TO TAKE
AWAY YOUR FIRST AMENDMENT
RIGHTS, SECONDMENT RIGHTS BUT
THEY WANT TO GIVE VOTING RIGHTS
TO TERRORISTS.
>> Juan: ARE YOU OKAY?
>> Jesse: I'M GREAT■.
>> Greg: EMILY.
>> Juan: DEMOCRATS GOT MORE
VOTES THAN THE REPUBLICANS IN
2016.
>> Jesse: NOT IN THE RIGHT
STATES.
>> Greg: ALL OF THEM WERE
FELONS OR AT LEAST LIVING IN
CALIFORNIA.
I AM FROM CALIFORNIA.
EMILY, YOU CLAIM TO BE A LAWYER.
>> Emily: YES.
>> Greg: WHAT ARE YOUR
THOUGHTS?
>> Emily: I FEEL SO STRONGLY
ABOUT THIS.
LET'S KEEP IT TO THE MOMENT TO
THE PRESENTLY INCARCERATED.
YOU MAKE GREAT POINTS.
6 MILLION PEOPLE A YEAR THAT HER
POST-CONVICTION FELONS.
I THINK IT RAISES A LOT OF GREAT
QUESTIONS.
WHY DO WE CONDEMN OUR
INCARCERATED TO CIVIC --
WHY DO WE TAKE AWAY THEIR RIGHT
TO VOTE?
WHY DO WE SUPPORT A PRISON-BASED
GERRYMANDERING WHEN PEOPLE
INCARCERATED ARE COUNTED IN THE
LEGISLATIVE DISTRICT.
>> Greg: THAT IS NOT WHAT
BERNIE IS TALKING ABOUT.
BERNIE IS TALKING ABOUT LETTING
A TERRORIST VOTE WHILE HE'S IN
JAIL.
>> Juan: HE IS A CITIZEN STILL
STILL.
>> Greg: HE IS IN PRISON.
>> Emily: I WANT TO DRAW THE
DISTINCTION THAT YOU CAN
ABSOLUTELY DISTINGUISH VIOLENT
CRIME, CONVICTS AND WHEN YOU
REDUCE IT TO THE TINY PERCENTAGE
OF THE SERIAL RAPIST AND
BOMBERS, ABSOLUTELY NOT.
BUT TO RECOGNIZE THOSE
INCARCERATED, A BIPARTISAN
COMMITMENT TO CRIMINAL JUSTICE
REFORM, WHO BETTER TO
PARTICIPATE POTENTIALLY THAN
THOSE PRESENTLY INCARCERATED
IS IT THE 3/5 CONSTITUTIONAL
CLAUSE ALL OVER AGAIN?
>> Greg: THAT WOULD BE A LOUSY
ARGUMENT, EMILY.
>> Dana: I THINK WE ARE
MISSING ONE OF THE MOST
IMPORTANT THINGS LAST NIGHT, AND
THAT IS THAT BERNIE, YES, HE
SAID THAT.
THAT WAS HIS INSTINCT.
DON'T THINK THEY WERE
ANTICIPATING THE QUESTION.
MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIEG HAD A
DIFFERENT ANSWER.
>> Greg: WOULD YOU LIKE TO
HEAR IT?
>> Dana: YES, PLEASE.
>> Greg: LET'S PLAY THAT TAPE
FOR DANA.
>> PART OF THE PUNISHMENT WHEN
YOU'RE CONVICTED OF A CRIME IN
YOUR INCARCERATED IS, YOU LOSE
CERTAIN RIGHTS.
YOU LOSE YOUR FREEDOM.
I THINK DURING THAT PERIOD, IT
DOES NOT MAKE SENSE TO HAVE AN
EXCEPTION FOR THE RIGHT TO VOTE.
>> AND PEOPLE LEAVE THE PRISON
SYSTEM, THEY NEED TO BE
REINTEGRATED INTO THEIR
COMMUNITIES.
THEY NEED TO BE ABLE TO HAVE A
CHANCE TO GET A JOB, TO BE ABLE
TO FIND DECENT HOUSING, AND THEY
NEED TO BE ABLE TO PARTICIPATE
IN THE POLITICAL PROCESS, THAT
MEANS THEY NEED THE RIGHT■■ TO
VOTE TO BE REINSTATED.
>> Dana: ELIZABETH WARREN, SHE
IS TRYING TO SOLVE A DIFFERENT
PROBLEM AND THAT'S THAT AFTER
YOU'VE SERVED YOUR DEBT TO
SOCIETY.
IF WE BELIEVE THAT VOTING IS A
PRIVILEGE OF YOUR CITIZENSHIP,
THERE HAS TO BE SOME SORT OF
PUNISHMENT FOR COMMITTING A
CRIME.
IN FLORIDA, THERE WERE A LOT OF
REPUBLICANS THAT VOTED FOR
RESTORING VOTING RIGHTS TO
FELONS.
THEY MADE A COUPLE EXCEPTIONS
FOR VIOLENT CRIME AND
SEXUAL ASSAULT BUT THAT'S
TOTALLY DIFFERENT FROM PEOPLE
BEING ABLE TO VOTE IN PRISON.
I THINK MAYOR PETE HAD A MUCH
BETTER ANSWER THAN BERNIE LAST
NIGHT.
>> Greg: I THINK THAT WIFE
MAYOR PETE IS RISING, BUT
BECAUSE HE'S NOT CRAZY.
>> Emily: IS IT A PRIVILEGE OR
AS A RIGHT?
A CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHT?
>> Juan: IT IS IN THE
CONSTITUTION.
>> IF YOU ARE A
TERRORIST AND YOU BOMB CIVILIAN
CIVILIANS.
>> Greg: I DON'T MIND TAKING
THAT RIGHT OR PRIVILEGE TAKEN
AWAY.
THEY ARE IN A BOX.
DO YOU THINK THEY REALLY CARE
ABOUT VOTING?
THEY ALREADY CAN'T LEAVE.
I DON'T SEE -- WE ARE ARGUING
OVER SOMETHING SO STUPID.
>> Emily: I SPENT A LOT OF
TIME WITH INMATES AND THEY DO
CARE.
I THINK THAT'S WHY, THOSE
STUDIES HAVE SHOWN THEY MIGHT
TURN TOWARDS THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
I DO FEEL LIKE A LOT OF THEM
BASED ON THEIR EXPERIENCE ARE
WHOLEHEARTEDLY FOR LIMITED
GOVERNMENT AND LIMITED
OVERREACH.
THEY ARE RECEIVING THE BRUNT OF
IT.
>> Greg: NOW YOU CHANGED MY
MIND.
>> Juan: YOU CAME TO ME FOR
THERAPY AND I'M CRAZY NOW.
YOU CHANGED MY MIND.
>> Greg:   AFTER SEVERAL BOTCHED
ROLLOUTS, JOE BIDEN SAYS HE'S
FINALLY READY TO JUMP INTO THE
2020 RACE.
THE LATEST NEXT.
I wanna keep doing what I love,
that's the retirement plan.
With my annuity,
I know there is a guarantee.
It's for my family,
its for my self,
its for my future.
Annuities can provide
protected income for life.
Learn more at
Retire Your Risk dot org.
This is not a bed...
it's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed, from $999,
intelligently senses
your movement and
automatically adjusts to
keep you both comfortable.
And now, save $400 on select
Sleep Number 360 smart beds.
Plus free premium delivery
when you add a base.
Ends Saturday.
We humans are
strange creatures.
Other species avoid pain
And struggle.
We actually... seek it out.
Other species do
difficult things
Because they have to.■
We do difficult things.
Because we like to.
We think it's... fun.
Introducing the all-new
2019 Ford Ranger
Built for the strangest
of all creatures.
Since you're heading off to
school, I got you this Brita.
Dad... I just got a ZeroWater.
But we've always used Brita.
it's two stage-filter...
doesn't compare to ZeroWater's
5-stage.
This meter shows how much
stuff,
or dissolved solids, gets left
behind.
Our tap water is 220.
Brita? 110...
Seriously?
but ZeroWater-
Let me guess. Zero?
Yup, that's how I know it is
the purest-tasting water.
I need to find the
receipt for that.
Oh yeah, you do.
I can't believe it.
That we're playing
“four on four”
with a barbershop quartet?
[QUARTET SINGING]
Bum bum bum bum...
pass the ball... pass the rock..
...we're open
just pass the ball!
No, I can't believe how easy it
was to save hundreds of dollars
on my car
insurance with GEICO.
Yea.
[QUARTET SINGING]
Shoot the J! Shoot, shoot,
shoot the jaaaaaay...
Believe it! GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
or more on car insurance.
HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN'T GET
HIGH SPEED INTERNET WHERE YOU
LIVE? WELL YOU CAN, WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITE INTERNET WHEREVER YOU
LIVE. HUGHESNET GEN 5 IS FAST.
YOU'LL GET 25MBPS, PLUS BUILT-IN
WI-FI, AND THERE'S NO HARD DATA
LIMITS. SO, WHEREVER YOU LIVE,
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
EVERYTHING YOU LOVE ONLINE.
CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, STAY
INFORMED, WATCH THE LATEST
VIDEOS, AND HELP YOUR KIDS GET■
■■■■■■NDER HUG■
AMERICA'S NUMBER ONE CHOICE FOR
SATELLITE INTERNET. ACT NOW TO
SAVE BIG WITH OUR LIMITED TIME
OFFER. GET FREE STANDARD
INSTALLATION BY CALLING RIGHT
NOW. SO, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING
FOR? GET HUGHESNET GEN5. TO
ORDER, CALL THE NUMBER ON YOUR
SCREEN. BE SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR
HOME PHONE SERVICE, TOO. CALL
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN
TODAY.
♪ ♪
>> Juan: IT LOOKS LIKE JOE IS
FINALLY AGO.
SOURCES SAY JOE BIDEN WILL MAKE
HIS LONG-AWAITED 2020
PRESIDENTIAL ANNOUNCEMENT
THURSDAY.
HE WILL THEN MAKE HIS FIRST
APPEARANCE AS AN OFFICIAL
CANDIDATE NEXT WEEK IN
PITTSBURGH.
THE CAMPAIGN ROLLOUT HAS BEEN
FAR FROM PERFECT.
IT'S BEEN PLAGUED BY DELAYS, FOR
EXAMPLE.
ONE FORMER AIDE REPORTEDLY
SAYING "I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
SO -- THEY ARE IMPROVISING AND
DOING LAST-MINUTE PLANNING.
THE GUY'S BEEN RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT SINCE MATE 77 AND
CAN'T FIGURE OUT THE BASICS LIKE
WHERE TO STAND ON HIS FIRST DAY.
THIS SHOULD MAKE EVERYONE VERY
NERVOUS."
A NEW NATIONAL POLL HAS BIDEN
LEADING THE PACK WITH 27%.
YOU CAN SEE THE NUMBERS.
SO JESSE, QUICK QUESTION.
ARE REPUBLICANS SCARED OF
JOE BIDEN?
>> Jesse: I DON'T THINK THEY
ARE SCARED OF HIM.
I THINK REPUBLICANS RESPECT
BIDE WHAT DONE.
HE HAS APPEAL THAT NEEDS TO BE
RECOGNIZED.
AT THE SAME TIME, THE GUY HAS
GOT TERRIBLE TIMING, POOR
INSTINCTS, AND HAS COAST ABOUT
OBAMA'S COATTAILS FOR THE LAST
I■■ DON'T THINK HE HAS THE GENEO
MANAGE A PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE SOMETHING THAT
SAYS I'M A GOOD MANAGER.
BIDEN HAS NEVER SHOWN AN ABILITY
TO MANAGE ANYTHING.
YOU HAVE TO CREATE A HIERARCHY.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE DISCIPLINE.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE SOME SORT OF
ATTENTION TO DETAIL.
HE IS A■■■■■■■■■ CHARMING GUY, S
NOT PROFICIENT AND HE DOESN'T
HAVE THE SKILLS TO MANAGE A
PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN.
THAT'S WHY IT'S SO SLOPPY.
I WILL POINT OUT ONE THING THAT
HE IS LAUNCHING IN PITTSBURGH
WHICH IS INTERESTING.
PENNSYLVANIA.
KAMALA AND SANDERS HAVE ALSO
BEEN IN PENNSYLVANIA AND
MICHIGAN AND WISCONSIN.
PRESIDENT TRUMP JUST GOT BACK
FROM MICHIGAN AND I WAS GOING TO
WISCONSIN THIS WEEKEND.
EVERYTHING IS TAKING PLACE ON
THE DEMOCRATS' TURF AND THAT'S
NOT A GOOD PLACE FOR THE
DEMOCRATS TO BE.
THEY ARE SO UNDER PRESSURE TO
WIN AND THEIR OWN BLUE STATES
THAT IT'S GOING TO BE HARD FOR
THEM BECAUSE THEY'RE GOING TO BE
SPREAD TOO THIN FINANCIALLY.
>> Juan: DANA, LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE ROLLOUT.
HE SAW THE COMMENTS, VERY SORT
OF DERISIVE, SAYING HE DOESN'T
KNOW WHAT HE'S DOING.
LET ME TELL YOU THE SCENE THAT
THEY ARE LOOKING AT IS THE
BATTLE FOR THE SOUL OF AMERICA
AND THEY ARE CONSIDERING NOT
ONLY WILL THERE BE A VIDEO ON
THURSDAY MORNING BUT POSSIBLY
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE BIDEN ON
THE STEPS OF THE PHILADELPHIA
ART MUSEUM, LIKE ROCKY, I'M
READY TO GO.
THEN THE QUESTION IT, DOES HE GO
TO D.C., DELAWARE?
THEY ROLLED OUT CHARLOTTESVILLE,
VIRGINIA, WHERE THAT TERRIBLE
INCIDENT TOOK PLACE.
WHAT YOU THINK?
>> Dana: THE ROLLOUT, IF
YOU'RE FOLLOWING IT EVERY DAY
AND YOU'RE WAITING FOR HIM TO
ANNOUNCE, IT LOOKS VERY SLOPPY
AND SHAKY.
IF YOU LOOK AT THE POLL, PEOPLE
THAT ARE DEMOCRATIC VOTERS LOOK
AT IT AND SAY THEY LIKE HIM.
I THINK MAYBE WHEN WE ARE
COVERING IT EVERY SINGLE DAY, TO
STEP BACK AND LOOK AT THE BIGGER
PICTURE FOR HIM.
THE FORMER AIDE TO GIVE THAT■■Oo
SOMEBODY WHO WAS ACTUALLY ON
PRESIDENT OBAMA'S TEAM.
OFTEN, THERE'S THE TENSION
BETWEEN THE PRESIDENTS TEAM
VERSUS THE VICE PRESIDENT'S
TEAM.
NOT AN HOURLY ADMINISTRATION, OF
COURSE.
THEN YOU CAN LOOKCALLY
UPON SOMEBODY'S EFFORTS.
IT■ MAKES ME WONDER IF THERE ARE
SOME OBAMA PEOPLE WHO ARE GOING
TO HOLD BACK SUPPORT FOR BIDEN
AND NOT COME OUT WITH HIM.
SOME PEOPLE HAVE GONE TO
MAYOR PETE.
I DON'T THINK ANY OF THEM WILL
WORK FOR BERNIE BUT THERE'S
DEFINITELY NOT A COHESIVE UNIT
BEHIND HIM FROM THE OBAMA TEAM.
>> Juan: LET ME PUT UP SOME
POLLS THAT WE CAN SHOW TO GREG.
>> Greg: I LOVE POLES, JUAN.
>> Juan: IN IOWA, IN FACT
BIDEN IS TIED WITH
BERNIE SANDERS, ACCORDING TO THE
DEMOCRATS VOTING.
HOW ABOUT IN NEW HAMPSHIRE?
HERE WE HAVE BERNIE SANDERS
LEADING ALMOST DOUBLE WHAT
JOE BIDEN HAS.
THEN YOU GET TO SOUTH CAROLINA,
BIDEN HAS A BIG LEAD.
NEVADA AGAIN.
BIDEN WITH THE LEAD.
EMILY, DO YOU WANT TO TAKE A
SHOT?
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THOSE POLLS?
>> Emily: SOME OF THOSE POLLS
HAVE INDICATED THAT BIDEN
SUPPORT HAS BEEN LITERALLY
HALVED IN THE LAST TEN DAYS.
AS AN ARGUMENT WHETHER THESE ARE
ACCURATE.
WE'VE BEEN FOOLED BY THE POLLS
BEFORE.
I THINK THAT CAN BE AN ARGUMENT
MADE THAT IS IT FUMBLING OR IS
IT METHODICAL AND STRATEGIC?
THEY ARE SO -- THEY DON'T WANT
TO MAKE A MISSTEP AND MAKE SURE
EVERYTHING'S RIGHT.
MAYBE IT'S AN INDICATION THAT
THEY'RE BEING REALLY SCRUPULOUS
AND I THINK I WONDER MOVING
FORWARD, ALTHOUGH OBAMA HASN'T
EXPRESSED SUPPORT AT THIS POINT,
MAYBE IT'S BIDEN THAT WOULD GET
THE OBAMA AND CLINTON MONEY THAT
HE WOULD BE THE BENEFIT OF THAT.
WE KNOW OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
IS KIND OF HATING BERNIE RIGHT
NOW BUT BIDEN MIGHT BE THE
CANDIDATE, WHAT IF IT'S CONOR
LAM SITUATION WHERE HE IS
REPRESENTING THE G.O.P. LEANING
GERRYMANDERING DISTRICTS THAT
WERE KIND OF
ANTI-HILLARY CLINTON.
HAVE THEY'VE SEEN BENEFITS FROM
THIS ADMINISTRATION PERSONALLY?
WOULD HE DETRACT FROM THAT?
I'M FULL OF QUESTIONS AND NO
ANSWERS.
>> Greg: I WILL TRY TO ANSWER
ALL OF YOUR QUESTIONS.
I'M AMAZED HOW QUICKLY BETO IS
DISAPPEARING SINCE BUTTIGIEG
CAME IN.
DISAPPEARING FASTER THAN A
TWINKIE ON MICHAEL MOORE'S LAP.
HAVEN'T USE THAT ONE IN A WHILE.
BIDEN REMINDS ME OF THE SEINFELD
EPISODE WHERE A PERSON CAN
APPEAR ATTRACTIVE DEPENDING ON
THE LIGHTING.
SOMETIMES YOU LOOK AT BIDEN A
NEW GO YOU KNOW WHAT, HE'S
APPEALING.
HE'S MODERATE, SENSIBLE.
SEEMS KIND OF HAS AN AIR OF
CONFIDENCE ABOUT HIM.
WHEN YOU SEE THEM AGAIN AND YOU
THINK NO, HE'S CLUMSY.
HE'S NOT VERY BRIGHT.
HE COULD BE AN ABSOLUTE
DISASTER.
HE'S KIND OF LIKE VEERING FROM
ONE TO THE OTHER.
POLITICAL PIG PEN.
GOT A BIG CLOUD OF DUST
FOLLOWING HIM.
A SENSE OF AGE, IRRELEVANCE,
DECISION.
I CAN FEEL THE PARTY DOESN'T
WANT HIM.
WE HAVE TO TALK ABOUT HIM DOING
THE VIDEO.
HE DID A VIDEO TO RULE OUT ANY
MISTAKES.
WHEN YOU DO A PRETAPE FOR TV, A
REALLY BAD GUEST.
>> Dana: NOT COMING DOWN THE
ESCALATOR.
>> Greg: THEY DIDN'T WANT TO
TRUST THAT HE MIGHT NOT FALL
DOWN ESCALATOR.
BUT WE MADE FUN OF TRUMP FOR
BEING CHAOTIC, FOR BEING --
>> Jesse: WE DID?
>> Greg: I'M SURE I DID.
I THINK I MADE FUN OF GOING DOWN
THE ESCALATOR.
I THINK I SAID HIS CAMPAIGN WAS
OVER WHEN HE WENT DOWN
ESCALATOR.
I CAN TELL YOU WHEN I'M WRONG.
>> Dana: WE STARTED OUR SHOW
TODAY WITH THE BERNIE COMMENTS.
HE IS TEFLON FOR THE DEMOCRATS.
HIS BASE, THEIR UNSHAKABLE.
>> Juan: ONE LAST THING, YOU
SAID DEMOCRATS REALLY DON'T WANT
HIM.
POLLS INDICATE THEY DO.
>> Greg: I THINK THE NAME
RECOGNITION, I DON'T KNOW.
I STILL PUT MONEY ON KAMALA.
I'M JUST GOT FEELING.
>> Jesse: THE PRONUNCIATION.
>> Greg: WHAT ABOUT KRISTEN
GILLIBRAND?
>> Juan: WE ARE GOING TO PUT
THE U BACK IN YOUR NAME.
>> Jesse: OH!
>> Juan: HILLARY CLINTON
HAMMERING PRESIDENT TRUMP OVER
THE MUELLER REPORT.
WHAT SHE IS SAYING ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT NEXT.
THAT'S HERE FOR YOU ON
"THE FIVE" ."
■ú■ú■■■& & ■&■■&■■
I don't keep track of regrets.
I never count the wrinkles.
And I don't add up the years.
But what I do count on...
is staying happy and healthy.
So, I add protein,
vitamins and minerals to my diet
BOOST®.
Delicious BOOST®
High Protein Nutritional Drink
has 20 grams of protein,
along with 26 essential
vitamins and minerals
your body needs.
All with guaranteed great taste.
The upside-
I'm just getting started.
BOOST® High Protein.
Be Up For Life™.
Look for savings on BOOST®
in your Sunday paper.
■■
This is Huntsville, Alabama.
AKA, Rocket City, USA.
This is a very difficult job.
Failure is not an option.
More than half of employees
across the country
bring financial stress to work.
If you're stressed out
financially at home,
you're going to be too worried
to be able to do a good job.
I want to be able to offer all
of the benefits
that keep them satisfied.
It is the people that is really
the only asset that you
Put your employees on a path
ellness
with Prudential.
Bring your chall
♪ ♪
>> Jesse: STEVEN MOORE 2020
DEMOCRATS ARE DRIBBLING ON THE
TRUMP IMPEACHMENT TRAIN.
>> IF ANY OTHER HUMAN BEING IN
THIS COUNTRY HAD DONE WHAT'S
DOCUMENTED IN THE MUELLER
REPORT, THEY WOULD BE ARRESTED
AND PUT IN JAIL.
>> I BELIEVE WE NEED TO GET RID
OF THIS PRESIDENT.
I BELIEVE CONGRESS SHOULD TAKE
STEPS TOWARDS IMPEACHMENT.
>> I THINK HE'S MADE IT PRETTY
CLEAR THAT HE DESERVES
IMPEACHMENT.
I'M GOING TO LEVERAGE THE HOUSE
AND SENATE TO FIGURE IT OUT.
>> Jesse: HILLARY CLINTON
GETTING IN ON THE ACTION SHOWING
SHE IS STILL NOT OVER 2016, SHE
WAS ACTUALLY CLAIMING THAT
MUELLER WAS TOO EASY ON FRONT,
EVEN AFTER THE FBI GAVE HER A
FREE PASS.
>> I THINK THERE'S ENOUGH THERE
THAN ANY OTHER PERSON WHO HAD
ENGAGED IN THOSE ACTS WOULD
CERTAINLY HAVE BEEN INDICTED.
AS I READ IT, WHAT I THOUGHT IT
WAS SAYING WAS WE THINK HE
OBSTRUCTED JUSTICE.
HERE ARE 11 EXAMPLES OF WHY WE
THINK HE OBSTRUCTED JUSTICE.
YOU COULD NOT BE MORE EXPLICIT
THEN PLEASE, LOOK AT THIS LOOK
AT IT AND CONCLUDED DOESN'T
RISE TO IMPEACHABLE OFFENSE.
THAT'S YOUR JOB.
BUT I'M GIVING THIS TO YOU.
>> Jesse: DANA, TRUMP WAS
INVESTIGATED FOR CRIME THAT
NEVER EXISTED.
I DON'T SEE HOW DEMOCRATS CAN
TAKE THIS AND RUN WITH IT.
>> Dana: IT'S INTERESTING THAT
BERNIE AND NANCY PELOSI ARE
LEADING THE ANTI-IMPEACHMENT
CHARGE.
>> Jesse: VERY INTERESTING.
>> Dana: THE ALSO HAVE THE OLD
GUARD VERSUS THE NEW GUARD.
THE NEW GUARD IS SAYING WE ARE
NOT BEHOLDEN TO HISTORY AND WHAT
HAPPENED WITH BILL CLINTON AND
THE REPUBLICANS FAILED ATTEMPTS
TO IMPEACH THE PRESIDENT, GET
RID OF BILL CLINTON.
WHEN NOT BEHOLDEN TO THAT.
WE WANT AND PRIMARY VOTERS SAY
WE WANT IMPEACHMENT TO BE AT
LEAST ATTEMPTED.
SMART PEOPLE GO, IT'S NOT GOING
TO HAPPEN IN THE SENATE.
BY THE TIME THEY GET TO THAT
POINT, WELL INTO THE END OF THIS
YEAR, NEXT YEAR, PRESIDENT TRUMP
IS OFF TO THE RACES AND PROBABLY
HITTING ALTHOUGH SPOTS THAT YOU
JUST TALKED ABOUT IN THE MIDWEST
AND THAT'S WHY THINK SOMEONE
LIKE MAYOR PETE, HE SAYS YEAH, I
THINK WE SHOULD NOT HAVE THIS
PRESIDENT BUT I'M GOING TO LET
THE HOUSE AND SENATE DEAL WITH
IT.
HE SIDESTEPS IT.
>> Jesse: MAYOR PETE IS
LOOKING GOOD ON "THE FIVE"
TODAY.
VERY IMPRESSIVE.
ISN'T HE DOING A TOWN HALL WITH
FOX NEWS?
>> Greg: HE IS.
THE BAR IS SO LOW FOR CHARISMA.
THERE'S NO CHARISMA ON THAT
STAGE AND I THINK MAYOR PETE IS
IN THE TOP LEVEL OF CHARISMA.
HE SEEMS KIND OF AT EASE WITH
HIMSELF.
COMPARED TO LIZ WARREN.
OF FERN IS CHARISMATIC.
THE DEMOCRATS ARE LIKE DRUNK AT
A PARTY THAT DOESN'T HAVE ANY
BOOZE.
SO THEY ARE IN YOUR BATHROOM
INGESTING HAND DISINFECTANT AND
MOUTHWASH.
YOU HAVE THE BOOMING ECONOMY,
LOW UNEMPLOYMENT, A STRONG
DEFENSE.
AND YOU'VE GOT AMERICA THAT'S
RESPECTED AND FEARED FOR ONCE.
NOT MUCH LEFT ON THE TABLE FOR
YOU TO DRINK.
SO IMPEACHMENT IS THAT HAND
DISINFECTANT AND THE MOUTH
MOUTHWASH IN THE BATHROOM.
>> Jesse: WHEN YOU INVITE GREG
TO A PARTY, MAKE SURE YOU HAVE
ALCOHOL.
HE WILL GO THROUGH YOUR
CABINETS.
DEMOCRATS DIVIDED ON
IMPEACHMENT.
IT LOOKS WEAK THAT THEY CAN'T
DECIDE WHICH WAY TO GO.
IF YOU HAVE IT LOOKS WEAK AND
ISAAC IS WASTING TIME AND
RESOURCES.
WE DISCUSSED IT BEFORE, THAT MY
OPINION, THE COLOSSAL EFFORT
WOULD TAKE AN EVEN NANCY PELOSI
SAYING THERE'S KIND OF A LOT OF
STEPS FROM 0 TO RAMP TO 100.
THERE'S A LOT OF WAYS TO PROBE
AND INVESTIGATE.
THAT'S ALL A WASTE OF TIME.
IT'S A WASTE OF TIME.
IT NEEDS ARE NOT LEGISLATING.
HILLARY CLINTON, IT WAS
DISTURBING TO ME THAT IT LACKED
SPECIFICITY AND THE
INTELLECTUALISM THAT SHE COULD
HAVE SHINES.
I DON'T SEE MAYOR PETE'S
RESPONSE SIDESTEPPING IT.
WHAT'S THE WORD, YOU DELEGATE.
LET THEM DO THEIR JOB.
THAT'S WHAT THEY ELECTED HIM
FOR.
THEIR OPINION MATTERS.
>> Jesse: BECAUSE HE IS A
MAYOR, HE CAN JUST DELEGATED TO
THE HOUSE AND SENATE.
HOUSE AND SENATE, HE TURNED OVER
EVERYTHING.
WHAT DID HE OBSTRUCT?
>> Juan: YOU SHOULD READ THE
REPORT.
>> Jesse: WHAT DID HE
OBSTRUCT?
>> Juan: HE WAS TRYING TO
OBSTRUCT THE MUELLER PROBE IN
THE INVESTIGATION.
>> Jesse: YOU WANT TO IMPEACH
HIM FOR NOT FIRING THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL?
SEVEN IN FACT, THE ARGUMENT
COMING OUT OF THE TRUMP
WHITE HOUSE IS ATTACKING DONALD
McGAHN BECAUSE HE'S THE ONE
WHO TOLD THE STORY TO MUELLER.
HE'S GOING TO TELL THE STORY IN
FRONT --
>> Jesse: I AM TRYING TO DO
SOMETHING WHICH HE HAS PERFECTLY
LEGAL RESPONSIBILITY TO DO.
>> Jesse: DO YOU REMEMBER LAST
NIGHT, GREG WAS WORRIED ABOUT MY
TREMORS AND NIGHTMARES.
I THINK YOUR LIVING A NIGHTMARE.
LET'S GET TO THIS TOPIC.
YOU ACT SAFE REPUBLICANS VOTE IN
DEMOCRATIC PRIMARIES.
GUESS WHAT.
IT'S JUST DEMOCRATS.
IT'S LIKE 70% OF DEMOCRATS WHO
SAY CONTINUE THE INVESTIGATION.
CONTINUE THE INVESTIGATION.
MORE THAN HALF WANT TRUMP
IMPEACHED.
WHAT YOU'RE SEEING IS THAT THE
CANDIDATES ARE RESPONDING TO THE
FACT THAT MOST DEMOCRATS WANT TO
SEE THEM NOT LAY DOWN BUT PLAY
THE HARDBALL AND THE CHEATING
THAT GOES ON AMONG REPUBLICANS.
>> Jesse: IN PEACH BEFORE THE
REPORT CAME OUT?
>> Juan: THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I WILL SAY WHEN YOU LOOK AT
INDEPENDENTS WHO ARE CRITICAL
COHORTS, IF YOU'RE LOOKING AT
THE 2020 ELECTION, WHAT YOU SEE
THERE IS 44% OPPOSE IMPEACHMENT.
>> Jesse: JUAN, I'M TALKING TO
YOU.
I THINK -- --
UP NEXT, IF YOU THOUGHT
DEMOCRATS WERE DONE WITH
RIDICULOUS GREEN NEW DEAL
PROPOSALS, THINK AGAIN.
I can't tell you who I am
or what I witnessed,
but I can tell you Liberty
Mutual customized my
car insurance so I only
pay for what I need.
Oh no, no, no, no,
no, no, no...
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
♪♪
Every day,
So, every day,
♪♪
The United States
Postal Service makes
more e-commerce
deliveries to homes
than anyone else
in the.
♪♪
Because the future only
happens with people
who really know how
to deliver it.
I wanted more from
my COPD medicine...
...that's why I've got the
Power of 1 2 3 medicines
with TRELEGY.
The only FDA-approved
3-in-1 COPD treatment .
♪TRELEGY.♪
♪The Power of 1-2-3.♪
♪TRELEGY 1-2-3 TRELEGY.♪
■■00■■■■MMóKM■■■>8>x>x>x>x>x>■>,
♪The Power of 1-2-3.♪
I'm breathing better.
TRELEGY works 3 ways to...
...open airways,...
...keep them open...
...and reduce inflammation...
...for 24 hours
of better breathing.
TRELEGY won't replace a
rescue inhaler for sudden
breathing problems.
TRELEGY is NOT for asthma.
Tell your doctor if you have
a heart condition or
high blood pressure
before taking it.
Do not take TRELEGY
more than prescribed.
TRELEGY may increase
your risk of thrush,
pneumonia, and osteoporosis.
E  Call yeWeWeW■F■Fdthing, ches,
TRELEGY may increase
your risk of thrush,
mouth or tongue swelling
...problems urinating,
vision changes,
or eye pain occur.
Maybe you should think again.
Ask your doctor about
once-daily TRELEGY and
the Power of 1 2 3.
♪TRELEGY 1-2-3 ♪
Save at TRELEGY.com
What makes these simple dishes
the best simple dishes ever?
Great tasting, heart-healthy
California Walnuts.
♪TRELEGY 1-2-3 ♪
So simple, so good.
Get the recipes at walnuts.org.
>> Dana: TEAL
■
TAKE FOR>L>LXAMP HEREN
O UNVEILING A NEW
PROPOSAL■■BAN ICONIC
SKYSCRAPERS TO HELP FIGHT
CLIMATE CHANGE.
>> WE ARE ACTUALLY MAKING THE
GREEN NEW DEAL, LIVE HERE IN
NEW YORK CITY BECAUSE WE'RE
GOING TO BAN THE CLASSIC GLASS
AND STEEL SKYSCRAPERS WHICH ARE
INCREDIBLY INEFFICIENT RATE OF
SOME ALSO BUILD ONE, THEY CAN
TAKE STEPS TO MAKE IT
ENERGY-EFFICIENT BUT WE'RE NOT
GOING TO LIE WHAT WE USED TO SEE
IN THE PAST.
>> Dana: I GET IT, IN TERMS OF
ENERGY PRODUCTION, BUT HOW ARE
YOU GONNA BUILD A SKYSCRAPER
WITHOUT STEEL?
"THE NEW YORK POST" COVER MADE
ME LAUGH OUT LOUD.
THE STONE AGE.
I STILL SAY LAUGH OUT LOUD.
GREG, COME ON, HELP ME.
>> Greg: YOU COULD'VE SAVED
TIME, SAYING LOL.
>> Dana: IT'S THE SAME.
>> Greg: HE IS AN IDIOT.
WE KNOW THAT.
HE TAKES AN ENTIRE MOTORCADE
EVERY DAY FROM THE UPPER
EASTSIDE TO BROOKLYN TO THE GYM.
EVERYDAY HE DOES THIS.
HIS DEFENSE OF THIS PRACTICE IS
THAT HE HAS ENACTED ENERGY
POLICIES CITYWIDE THAT ALLOWS
HIM TO ABUSE HIS OWN BELIEFS.
I AM FORCING YOU, THE NEW YORK
CITIZEN, TO SACRIFICE SO I DON'T
HAVE TO.
IMAGINE A PERSONAL TRAINER WHO
WAKES YOU UP EVERY MORNING AND
DEMANDS THAT YOU DO GRIM ROUTINE
OF MILITARY STYLE BOOT CAMP
EXERCISES AND YOU GET UP OUT OF
BED AND YOU SEE THAT HE IS
MORBIDLY OBESE EATING THE
WORLD'S BIGGEST TOBY.
>> Dana: WE HAVE THE RESPONSE
FROM BILL de BLASIO ABOUT HIS
COMMUTE.
>> IT'S PART OF MY LIFE.
I COME FROM THAT NEIGHBORHOOD IN
BROOKLYN.
IT'S MY HOME.
I GO THERE ON A REGULAR BASIS TO
STAY CONNECTED WHY COME FROM AND
NOT BE IN THE BUBBLE THAT I
THINK IS A HUGE PROBLEM.
THE FACT IS THOSE CARS AND THAT
SECURITY DETAIL ARE PART OF THE
LIFE OF BEING MAYOR OF
NEW YORK CITY.
>> Dana: JESSE, GOT A GET AWAY
FROM SKYSCRAPERS AND GO TO
BROOKLYN GET OUT OF THE BUBBLE.
>> Jesse: I AM GLAD THAT HE'S
IN THE GYM.
HE'S NOT MESSING EVERYTHING UP
AT WORK.
THE GUY IS A LIAR.
ARE NOT BUI
APERS IN(ORK CITY
AN■%■%■%
NOT BECAUSE THEY'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO BUT BECAUSE HE KICKED AMAZON
OUT SO NO ONE WANTS TO DO
BUSINESS HERE ANYMORE.'S WORSE Y
IS FOR ME.
IT'S AN EMPTY GESTURE.
WHEN YOU ARE A MIRROR POLITICIAN
AND YOU LOSE AND LOSE AND LOSE,
DAY AFTER DAY AFTER DAY.
YOU HAVE TO FIGHT SOMETHING LIKE
GLOBAL WARMING.
YOU DECLARE VICTORY AND NO ONE
KNOWS AND NO ONE CAN KEEP COUNT
OF WHO'S WINNING AND LOSING.
GLOBAL WARMING IS NOT SOMETHING
THAT YOU NEED TO FIGHT.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING YOU CANINST.
NOT BUILDING A SKYSCRAPER, I AM
TEMPTED TO USE THE HORSE
ANALOGY.■;■;
THE PRODUCER WARNED MST
IT.
PROGRESSIVE THINK WHEN THEY ARE
MAKING PROGRESS, THEY DO THAT BY
GOING BACKWARDS.
I THINK THE STONE AGE THING
PERFECTLY ENCAPSULATED THAT.
>> Dana: EMILY, YOU DON'T LIVE
IN NEW YORK CITY.
YOU VISIT OFTEN.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> Emily: IT'S RIDICULOUS.
LIKE ALL OF THESE PLANS, WHEN
YOU LOOK AT THE SPECIFICS, IT'S
ABSOLUTELY ABSURD.
HE WAS LIKE THE HUDSON YARD WAS
BUILT AND THEN THE DEVELOPER
CAME OUT AND SAID THAT'S FUNNY
BECAUSE THE ALL GLASS BUILDING
IS LITERALLY CERTIFIED LEED
PLATINUM AND THE BANK OF AMERICA
BUILDING.
SOMEONE CALCULATED THAT ITS
CERTIFIED LEED PLATINUM AND
WOULD HAVE TO PAYÑÑ5 MILL
IN FINES.
THERE'S NOT ENOUGH CONTRACTORS
TO HAVE THESE 50,000 BUILDINGS
THAT THIS EFFECT BE BROUGHT UP
TO CODE.
WASTING EVERYONE'S TIME.
>> Dana: JUAN, I'M SURE THAT
YOU AGREE.
>> Juan: NOT AT ALL.
IN FACT, YOU GUYS ARE SO
APOPLECTIC.
WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID OF THE TERMS
OF A CONVERSATION?
[ALL SPEAKING]
YOU ARE LIKE OH, MY GOD.
>> Greg: I JUST STATED A FACT.
>> Juan: THE REALITY IS HE'S
TALKING ABOUT TIGHTENING THE
CODES SO THAT THEY ARE MORE
EFFICIENT.
>> Dana: HOW ABOUT PICKING UP
THE TRASH?
>> Juan: HE IS SAYING THAT IF
YOU'RE IN A SMALLER BUILDING,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PLAY BY THESE
RULES.
PUBLIC HOUSING, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO PLAY BY THESE RULES.
RENT CONTROL.
JESSE SAYS THEY'RE NOT BUILDING
SKYSCRAPERS.
YOU NEED TO WALK AROUND.
THEY ARE BUILDING SKYSCRAPERS
RIGHT HERE.
YOU CAN SEE ONE FROM THIS
STUDIO.
NEW YORK IS BOOMING AND GUESS
WHAT, PEOPLE WANT SOMETHING DONE
ON CLIMATE CHANGE.
REPUBLICANS HAVE NO PLAN.
YET THEY WANT TO SCREAM AT
EVERYONE ELSE WHO SAYS LET'S
HAVE SOME RATIONAL CONVERSATION
ABOUT HOW WE CAN DO BETTER IN
TERMS OF ENERGY EFFICIENCY.
>> Dana: 115 PEOPLE ARE
LEAVING THE CITY A DAY.
>> Jesse: ASK UNIONS IF THEY
WANT TO STOP BUILDING
SKYSCRAPERS.
>> Juan: NO ONE SAID STOP
BUILDING.
HE SAID TIGHTEN THE CODES.
>> Dana: CONTROVERSIAL NEW
PLAN BY STARBUCKS, THE CHAIN
ADDING NEEDLE DISPOSAL BOXES TO
S.
THAT'S UP NEXT ON
for up to 100% of
your home's value.
Thank You, Admiral.
So if you need money for your
family, call NewDay USA.
"Curiouser and
curiouser,"
a?         said Alice.
“The rabbit-hole
went straight on
like a tunnel for some way.”
"I've seen a cat without a gri,
but a grin without a cat.”
Hey, Mercedes, end audio.
Change lighting to soft blue.
The completely reimagined
2020 GLE.
With intelligent voice control
and available third row.
Your adventure awaits at the
Mercedes-Benz Spring Event
but hurry the event
ends April 30th.
(Burke)
At Farmers, we've seen almost
everything,
so we know how to
cover almost anything.
Even Rooftop Parking.
Strange forces at work?9/9/
Only if you're referring to
gravity-and we covered it.
Talk to Farmers.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
I have a vision
correction number,
But I'm more than a number.
When I'm not teaching,
I'm taking steep grades
and tight corners.
My Essilor lenses offer more
than vision correction
with three innovative
technologies
For my ultimate in vision
Clarity
And Protection
Together in a single lens:
The Essilor Ultimate
Lens Package.
So, I can do more
of what I love!
Buy two pairs of
Essilor's best lenses
and get a $100 back instantly.
See more. Do more. Essilor
There's brushing...and
there's Oral-B Power brushing.
Oral-B just cleans better.
Even my hygienist said
going electric could lead to way
cleaner teeth.
And unlike Sonicare,
Oral-B is the first electric
toothbrush brand
accepted by the ADA.
Oral-B.
Brush like a pro.
♪ ♪
>> Emily: STARBUCKS ROLLING
OUT OF CONTROVERSIAL PLAN IN■■■■
ADDING NEEDLE DISPOSAL BOXES.
THE BOXES ARE ALREADY IN 25
MARKETS WITH PLANS TO EXPAND THE
SUMMER.
AS STARBUCKS SPOKESPERSON
EXPLAINING "THE SOCIETAL ISSUES
AFFECT US ALL AND CAN SOMETIMES
PLACE OUR PARTNERS AND SCARY
SITUATIONS WHICH IS WHY WE HAVE
PROTOCOLS AND RESOURCES IN PLACE
TO ENSURE THAT OUR PARTNERS ARE
OUT OF HARM'S WAY."
THE CATALYST FOR THIS WAS
EMPLOYEES SIGNING A PETITION,
IT'S LIKE AN EMPLOYER RESPONDING
TO AN EMPLOYEE --
A WORKPLACE ACCOMMODATION
ALMOST.
SECONDLY, THE GOVERNMENT
INVESTIGATION THAT ENSUED AFTER
TWO WERE POKED BY SYRINGES IN
THE SAME MONTH.
>> Greg: IT'S ALL ABOUT THE
FEAR OF BEING SUED.
A CITY RUN BY THE LEFT, THE CITY
BECOMES A BATHROOM AND THE
BATHROOM BECOMES A SHOOTING
GALLERY.
BUSINESSES THAT ARE IN A BIND.
YOU WANT TO TREAT YOUR PROPERTY
THE WAY YOU WANTED TO BE
TREATED.
NO SHIRTS, NO SHOES, NO JUNKIES,
NO SERVICE.
THAT'S WHAT■, SAY.
BUT THEN YOU INCUR THE WRATH OF
THE WOKE.
SO YOU GIVE UP AND SAY FORGET
IT.
BUT THE BOXES IN THERE.
YOU FAILED TO UNDERSTAND THE
INCENTIVES THAT THE
WORD-OF-MOUTH IS THAT YOU CAN
SHOOT UP IN THE BATHROOM, YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE MORE PEOPLE
SHOOTING UP.
THAT'S THE WAY IT WORKS.
>> Juan: I THINK MOST
BUSINESSES THAT THEY HAVE
SEEN EVIDENCE OF DRUG USE IN
THEIR BATHROOMS, NOT JUST
STARBUCKS.
IT'S A REALITY.
A LOT OF BUSINESSES, IN ADDITION
TO HAVING EMERGENCY AID KITS,
HAVE SHARP KIDS.
STUCK ON THE WALL.ARILY■■■■■
ST IS SAYING THEY ARE
GOING TO PUT THEM ON THE WALL IN
THE BATHROOMS.
WHAT STRIKES ME IS STARBUCKS
RECENTLY SAID ANYBODY CAN USE
THE BATHROOMS.
IF■■ THAT, YOU KNOW WHAT,
YOU'RE GOING TO GET PEOPLE WHO
WANT TO MISBEHAVE.
SOME BARS YOU GO IN, THEY DON'T
HAVE A DOOR ON THE BATHROOM
STALL BECAUSE THEY ARE SO AWARE
OF PEOPLE DOING DRUGS IN THE
BATHROOM.
>> Greg: I HATE THOSE BARS.
>> Dana: I'VE NEVER BEEN TO
ONE OF THOSE.
>> Jesse: OBVIOUSLY NOT, DANA.
>> Emily: ONE YOU THINK ABOUT
THE ARGUMENT THAT
INCENTIVIZES --
>> Dana: THE POINT THAT I
WROTE DOWN IS, IS THE GOVERNMENT
FAILING IN THE PRIVATE SECTOR
HAS TO FIND A WAY TO DEAL WITH
IT?
WHEN STARBUCKS MADE THE
ANNOUNCEMENT, ALLOWING EVERYONE
TO COME AND USE THE BATHROOM, WE
ALL SAID IT'S INEVITABLE.
IS IT A PUBLIC SERVICE?
RETURNING -- ARE WE TURNING OUR
BUSINESSES INTO WHAT SHOULD BE A
GOVERNMENT RESPONSIBILITY?
IT SOUNDS LIKE IT.
>> Jesse: I WOULD NEVER
SECOND-GUESS A MULTINATIONAL
CORPORATION.
I THINK THEY ARE ALWAYS CORRECT
AND I THINK I'M GOING TO AGREE
WITH THEM THIS TIME.
IT'S LIKE HANDING OUT CONDOMS IN
HIGH SCHOOL.
PEOPLE HAVE THAT DEBATE, THEY'RE
GOING TO DO IT ANYWAY, YOU MIGHT
AS WILL HAVE THEM USE
PROTECTION.
I DON'T THINK JUNKIES ARE GOING
INTO STARBUCKS TO SHOOT UP
KNOWING THAT THEY CAN DISPOSE OF
THE NEEDLES.
I THINK THEY ARE TRYING TO
PROTECT THEIR EMPLOYEES FROM
GETTING POKED FROM A DIRTY
SYRINGE.
>> Emily: THE COST-BENEFIT L
ANALYSIS, THEIR RISK ASSOCIATED
WITH MAKING BLOOD CONTACT,
GETTING POKED, ONE OF THE
EMPLOYEES GET THE DISEASE?
>> Juan: YOU COULD GET HIV,
HEPATITIS.
>> Emily: IT'S WORSE
POTENTIALLY THAN THE MILLIONS
FOR INSTALLING IT.
IT'S ONLY IN CERTAIN MARKETS.
>> Jesse: PROBABLY IN
SAN FRANCISCO OR IN THE VILLAGE
OR SOMETHING.
IT'S NOT A WIDESPREAD.
>> Dana: THIS IS NOT HAPPENING
IN CHEYENNE.
>> Jesse: YOU EVER SEE HOW
NICE THE PEOPLE ARE THAT WORK AT
STARBUCKS?
THEY ARE THE NICEST PEOPLE.
>> Greg: WE KNOW WHAT YOU ARE
DOING.
YOU'RE TRYING TO GET A FREE
DRINK.
>> Jesse: I DON'T NEED A FREE
I CAN AFFORD AN ESPRESSO.
>> Emily: IS THAT WHAT YOU ARE
DOING?
[LAUGHTER]
WHATEVER.
"ONE MORE THING" IS UP NEXT, YOU
GUYS.
N■■■N■■■■■
Opening doors ologuard.
Turning 50 opens the
door to a lot of new things...
like now your doctor may be
talking to you
about screening
for colon cancer.
Luckily there's me,
Cologuard.
The noninvasive test
you use at home.
It all starts when your
doctor orders me.
Then it's as easy
as Get, Go, Gone.
You get me when I'm
delivered...
right to your front door
and in the privacy of your
own home.
There's no prep or
special diet needed.
You just go to the bathroom,
to colle■#r sample.
After that, I'm gone,
shipped to the lab for
DNA testing
that finds colon cancer
and precancer.
Cologuard is not right for
everyone.
It is not for high risk
individuals,
including those with a history
of colon cancer or precancer.
IBD, certain hereditary
cancer syndromes,
or a family history
of colon cancer.
Maybe I'll be at
your door soon!
Ask your doctor if
Cologuard is right for you.
Covered by Medicare
and most major insurers.
?á■■■■■■■■■■■■■■á■á■á■á?■á?■á■■■
Back then, we checked our
smartphones
zero times a day.
Times change. Eyes haven't.
That's why there's Ocuvite.
Screen light...
Sunlight...
Longer hours...
Eyes today are stressed!
But Ocuvite has vital
nutrients
to help protect them.
Ocuvite.
Eye nutrition for today.
♪♪
♪ ♪■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■x■■■■>> DanaO
ANOTHER I WANT TO CONGRATULATE
AUDREY, AN ARIZONA HIGH SCHOOLER
GOT A PERFECT SCORE ON HER ACT..
SHE HAS BEEN A AVID READER HER
WHOLE LIFE AND SHE ACCREDITS
THOUGHT FOR HELPING HER DO SO
WELL ON THE TEST.
WATCH THIS.
>> THAT WAS MY ESCAPE.
THAT WAS WHERE I GOT TO READ
MYSTERY NOVELS.
I LEFT THIS IDEA OF BEING
TRANSPORTED INTO ANOTHER WORLD.
I LOVE KNOWLEDGE SO MUCH.
I WANT TO GET THIS ANSWER RIGHT.
IT WAS NEVER HARD WORK.
IT WAS, I WANT TO DO THIS.
>> Dana: GOOD FOR AUDREY.
LAST YEAR, FEWER THAN 3800
RECEIVED A PERFECT SCORE.
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
>> Greg: I WATCHED JESSE ROLL
HIS EYES.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Dana: OR YOU CONCERNED
ABOUT ME?
>> Dana: WHY DID THEY CHOOSE
THAT FOR ME?
SHE TOOK THE TASK WITH HER DOG
AND GOT A PERFECT SCORE IN
WYOMING.
>> Jessie: TRUMP IMPERSONATOR
THE LONG ISLAND WORKER, WATCH
THE SKY.
>> THE LONG ISLAND REVEREND IS
SCREWING UP.
IT HAS A HORRIBLE JOB.
I'VE HIRED MY GOOD FRIEND
THESE ARE TREMENDOUS PEOPLE.
IF YOU CAN TELL YOU RIGHT NOW,
WE HAVE TO COME IN AND DO THIS
JOB ON TIME AND UNDER BUDGET.
THEY ARE GOOD PEOPLE.
[LAUGHTER]
THERE HE IS.
THOMAS LUNDY IS HIS NAME.
>> Juan: LAST WEEK WAS
SPRING BREAK FOR D.C. PUBLIC
SCHOOL KIDS SO WE TOOK A
VACATION.
I BROUGHT BACK SOME PICTURES.
HERE WE ARE AT THE AIRPORT AND
WE ARE ALL WEARING THE SAME
TRACKSUIT IN CASE YOU CAN'T
NOTICE.
SOME PEOPLE THOUGHT WE WERE A
SINGING GROUP.
WE GOT SO MUCH ATTENTION THAT
THE U.S. SURGEON GENERAL CAME
OVER AND TOOK THE PICTURE.
THEN IT WAS OFF TO BELIZE AND
HERE I AM WITH MY WIFE
OVERLOOKING THE CARIBBEAN.
HERE IS MY DAUGHTER WITH HER
HUSBAND ON THE GRANDKIDS.
HERE WE ARE WITH THE GRANDKIDS
AT A RESTAURANT IN THE POOL.
I GOT IN THE POOL TOO.
WE WERE OUT OF SNORKELING.
WE EVEN GOT TO JUMP IN WITH THE
SHARKS.
HERE THEY ARE LOOKING OVER THE
EDGE OF THE BOAT AS THE SHARKS
GATHERED BENEATH.
IT WAS A FUN TRIP AND I'M GLAD
TO BE PACKED.
ALSO IN THE GRAND CANYON'S OF
NEW YORK SKYSCRAPERS.
>> Jessie: STAYED AN EXTRA
WEEK IN BELIZE.
>> Juan: I WOULD BE GLAD TO.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Greg: I HAVEN'T DONE THIS
IN A WHILE.
I HATE THESE PEOPLE.
I MADE IT CLEAR HOW MUCH I
DESPISE TWITTER, BUT I'VE
REALIZED WHAT I DESPISE IT SO
MUCH.
IT IS BECAUSE NO MATTER WHAT
KIND OF PERSON YOU ARE YOU ARE A
LESSER PERSON ON TWITTER AND THE
REASON IS IT IS BECAUSE YOU
ELEVATE THE TRAUMA AND YOUR
MOTIONS.
HE MAY BE IN A NORMAL PERSON BUT
TWITTER YOU BECOME MRS. POWELL
OR THAT LADY IN THE THREE
STOOGES THAT ALWAYS GETS MAD AT
THE THREE STOOGES AND I CAN'T
REMEMBER HER NAME.
THAT IS WHAT YOU BECOME.
WHAT YOU SEE ON TWITTER RIGHT
NOW, PEOPLE ARE SAYING THAT I AM
LITERALLY SHAKING.
THEY SEE SOMETHING THEY DIDN'T
LIKE ON TV, I'M LITERALLY
SHAKING.
I AM IN TEARS, THEY ARE CRYING.
THERE ARE NO WORDS.
YOU ARE THE PROBLEM.
IF TWITTER IS GOING TO SURVIVE
PEOPLE HAVE TO DIAL BACK THIS
DRAMA BECAUSE IT IS SO REPULSIV
REPULSIVE.
SOMEBODY SAID THIS, IF JACK
DORSEY DECIDED TO ELIMINATE
TWITTER HE WOULD GET A NOBEL
PRIZE.
I DON'T KNOW WHO IS AT IT.
TAKE IT AWAY.
>> Emily: IN THIS AGE OF
WELLNESS, WE NOW HAVE WELLNESS
BEER.
THERE ARE A FEW COMPANIES ONE IN
PARTICULAR THAT REFERRED TO
THEMSELVES AS THE GATORADE OF
BEER.
IT HAS ALCOHOL IN IT.
>> Greg: THANK GOD FOR THAT.
SPACE SEEKS IT HAS ELECTROLYTES
AND BEE POLLEN AND ET CETERA.
[LAUGHTER]
SO AFTER A HARD WORKOUT YOU CAN
CELEBRATE WITH A BREW, BOTTOMS
UP.
THAT IS THE MAIN COMPANY THERE.
>> Greg: THAT IS A TERRIBLE