>> TIME FOR THE LAST BITE.
DURING TODAY'S WHITE HOUSE
EASTER APRIL DONALD TRUMP HAD A
SURPRISING CONVERSATION WHILE
HELPING KIDS COLOR CARDS.
A YOUNG GUY SAID HE IS BUILDING
THAT WALL.
DO YOU BE LEAVE HIM?
VERY CONSERVATIVE.
>> SOUNDS LIKE HE IS A
CONSERVATIVE.
I AM JASON CHAFFETZ IN FOR LAURA
INGRAM.
SHANNON, TAKE IT FROM HERE.
SHANNON: WE BEGIN WITH A FOX
NEWS ALERT.
DEMOCRATS UPPING THE ANTE,
ANOTHER SUBPOENA AND FACING
TOUGH QUESTIONS ABOUT THEIR
SEEMING UNWILLINGNESS TO
INVESTIGATE THE STEEL DOSSIER
WHICH THE NEW YORK TIMES SAYS IS
FULL OF FALSE CLAIMS FRONTED BY
HILLARY CLINTON AND THE DNC.
THE FIRST PRIMARY, BERNIE
SURGING IN THE POLLS AND SAYS
EVEN THE BOSTON MARATHON BOMBER
SHOULD GET THE VOTE FROM JAIL.
WE WAIT TO SEE IF JOE BIDEN
MAKES IT OFFICIAL THIS WEEK, WE
TALKED WHEN ACCUSER WHO SAYS THE
CONVERSATION SHE TRIED TO START
COULD BE DERAILED.
AND CHRISTIANS ATTACK ON THE
HOLIEST DAY IN SRI LANKA BY
RADICAL MUSLIMS AND MULTIPLE
REPORTS GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS NEW
OF THE POTENTIAL FOR THE TERROR
ATTACK WEEKS AGO.
SOME IN POWER STILL UNWILLING TO
CONNECT THE ATTACKS TO THEIR
CHRISTIAN FAITH IN.
I AM SHANNON BREAM IN
WASHINGTON.
LET'S GO TO ALRBER WHO
HAS MORE ON THE GROWING
CRITICISM OF THE STEEL DOSSIER
IN THE WEEK OF THE REPORT AND
DEMOCRATS GOING FOR IMPEACHMENT.
WE MONITOR WHAT HAPPENED AFTER A
CONFERENCE CALL.
172 DEMOCRATIC LAWMAKERS
PARTICIPATE IN A CONFERENCE
CALL, IT REPORTEDLY WENT ON FOR
90 MINUTES.
THE CALL WAS SPIRITED BUT THERE
WERE NO PLANS TO MOVE FORWARD
WITH IMPEACHMENT EVEN THOUGH
SOME PROGRESSIVE DEMOCRATS OF
CALLED FOR IT.
HERE IS HOW ONE DEMOCRAT
DESCRIBED THE CALL.
>> WE ARE NOT RUSHING TO
ANYTHING BUT WE KNOW THERE WERE
TROUBLESOME FINDINGS IN THE
MUELLER REPORT AND IT IS OUR JOB
TOññ■■■■■■■ SAID WHILE DEMOCRAT
FIRMLY AGREE WE SHOULD PROCEED
DOWN THE PATH OF FINDING THE
TRUTH IT IS IMPORTANT TO NOTE
FACTS REGARDING HOLDING THE
PRESIDENT ACCOUNTABLE CAN BE
GAINED OUTSIDE OF IMPEACHMENT
HEARINGS.
SOURCES SAY THAT IS WHAT SHE
REITERATED IN TONIGHT'S COLIN
HAS NOT RULED OUT THE
POSSIBILITY OF IMPEACHMENT.
NANCY PELOSI TOLD HER COLLEAGUES
THIS ISN'T ABOUT DEMOCRATS OR
REPUBLICANS BUT SAVING OUR
DEMOCRACY.
IF THAT IS WHERE THE FACTS TAKE
US THAT IS WHERE WE HAVE TO GO.
OTHER TOP DEMOCRATS WALKING A
SIMILAR LINE, NOT READY TO BEGIN
IMPEACHMENT MEETINGS WILL NOT
RULE IT OUT.
SOME LIKE JERRY NADLER SAY OTHER
THINGS NEED TO HAPPEN FIRST.
>> WE NEED TO HEAR FROM BAR, WE
NEED TO HEAR FROM MUELLER, WE
NEED THE ENTIRE REPORT IN ORDER
TO MAKE DECISIONS.
>> Reporter: THEY TRY TO FORCE
THEM TO PULL OVER THE ENTIRE
REPORT, ANNOUNCED ANOTHER
SUBPOENA, DON MCGANN, THE
CHAIRMAN IS ASKING FOR MORE
DOCUMENTS AND PUBLIC TESTIMONY
ON MAY 21ST.
WHEN IT COMES TO IMPEACHMENT
REPORTERS AT THE WHITE HOUSE
EASTER EGG ROLL ASKED DONALD
TRUMP IF HE'S WORRIED ABOUT IT,
SHANNON: THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AS DEMOCRATS FRET OVER HOW
IMPEACHMENT COULD IMPACT VOTER
SUPPORT, CANDIDATES APPEARED
DIVIDED AS THEY TRY TO GAUGE HOW
INDEPENDENTS ARE FEELING ABOUT
THE I WORD.
KRISTIN FISHER JOINS US FROM
MANCHESTER.
>> Reporter: 5 DEMOCRATIC
CONTENDERS HAVE BEEN FACING OFF
IN BACK TO BACK TOWNHALLS ON
CNN.
ALL OF THEM HAVE BEEN ASKED
ABOUT IMPEACHMENT AND ELIZABETH
MORAN SAYS SHE IS FOR IT BUT
LESS THAN AN HOUR AGO, SENATOR
KAMALA HARRIS JOINING HER BY
SAYING THIS.
>> I BELIEVE CONGRESS SHOULD
TAKE A STEP TOWARD IMPEACHMENT.
>> WARREN HAD CHALLENGED HER
COLLEAGUES TO TAKE A STAND ON
THE PRESIDENT'S ACTIONS DETAILED
IN THE MUELLER REPORT AND VOTE.
>> IF THERE ARE PEOPLE IN THE
HOUSE OR THE SENATE WHO WANT TO
SAY THAT IS WHAT A PRESIDENT CAN
DO WHEN THE PRESIDENT IS BEING
INVESTIGATED FOR HIS OWN
WRONGDOING OR A FOREIGN
GOVERNMENT TO TAX OUR COUNTRY
THE NATION HAS TO TAKE THAT A
VOTE AND LIVE WITH IT FOR THE
REST OF THEIR LIVES.
>> MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIEG'S
TOWNHALL IS STILL GOING ON BUT
THE OTHER TWO CANDIDATES WERE
PRETTY NONCOMMITTAL WHEN IT CAME
TO THE IMPEACHMENT QUESTION.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO PREDISPOSE
THINGS, I'M NOT GOING TO SAY IT
IS OR ISN'T BUT THERE ARE VERY
DISTURBING THINGS THAT WOULD
LEAD YOU TO BELIEVE THERE IS
INSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
>> OF THE NEXT YEAR AND A HALF
GOING INTO THE ELECTION ALL
CONGRESS IS TALKING ABOUT IS
IMPEACHING TRUMP AND TRUMP TRUMP
TRUMP AND MUELLER MUELLER
MUELLER AND WE ARE NOT TALKING
ABOUT HEALTHCARE OR RAISING THE
MINIMUM WAGE TO A LIVING WAGE,
WHAT I WORRY ABOUT IS THAT WORKS
TO TRUMP'S ADVANTAGE.
>> Reporter: ACCORDING TO A NEW
POLL BY THE UNIVERSITY OF NEW
HAMPSHIRE SANDERS IS LEADING THE
PACK IN THE FIRST PRIMARY STATE.
JOE BIDEN WHO MAY OR MAY NOT BE
ENTERING THE RACE IS 12 POINTS
BEHIND HIM AND THE RELATIVE
UNKNOWN TURNED RISING STAR PETER
BUTTIGIEG 3 POINTS BEHIND THE
FORMER VP.
EVERYONE ELSE'S IN SINGLE DIGITS
AND PEOPLE LOOK AT THE
REPUBLICAN FOOD AND NOT
SURPRISINGLY DONALD TRUMP IS
LIGHT YEARS AHEAD OF EVERYBODY
ELSE.
ONLY BILL WELLS HAS OFFICIALLY
ANNOUNCED PLANS TO CHALLENGE HIM
BUT THAT COULD CHANGE.
LARRY HOGAN WILL BE HERE
TOMORROW MORNING FOR
HAMPSHIRE TRADITION OF POLITICS
D WE■■ HIM
RIGHT AND EARLY.■■■■■■■■■■ñG■■■
ANNOUNCEMENT FROM JO
IN RACE THE WOMAN WHO
INITIATED A NATIONAL
CONVERSATION ABOUT HIS
INAPPROPRIATE TOUCHING HAS
PLENTY MORE TO SAY ABOUT HIS
ANTICIPATED CANDIDACY.
SHE JOINS US TONIGHT, WELCOME.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
SHANNON: I KNOW YOU WROTE DAYS
AGO ABOUT WHERE THIS
CONVERSATION WENT BECAUSE SOME
PEOPLE IMMEDIATELY REACTED
SAYING SHE IS NOT CLAIMING
SEXUAL ASSAULT OR SEXUAL
HARASSMENT AND ON THE OTHER
SIDE, HE IS A SERIAL HUGGER.
IS A GRAY AREA BETWEEN WHAT YOU
LOST?BEEN■■■■■■■■m■/zk8)8888
LOST?BEE■T■T■■L■L■L■L■■L■■■d■,■@
■I■I■I MORE
SERIOUS ■p■p■pERE THE CONVERSAT
DEVOLVED INTO BUT THAT IS NOT
WHERE IT STARTED.
WE TALKED ABOUT THE FACT THAT I
HAD NO PREVIOUS RELATIONSHIP
WITH THE VICE PRESIDENT, IT WAS
MOMENTS BEFORE HIGH PROFILE
EVENT WHERE I WAS SUPPOSED TO
SPEAK TO HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE.
HE WAS BEHIND ME.
HE HELD ONTO MY SHOULDERS, GOT
CLOSE TO MY BODY FROM ■2BE■Ç■LEN
■2 EVENT AND THAT IS NOT
■]■]                    ■]
■]■■■■Ûî
■z■z■z■z■z■Ç■zPz■z■z■zPzN TH■ÇÇ2
MY BIGGER POINT I'M TRYING TO
MAKE ■2■2■# ISN'T JUST
INAPPROPRIATE BEHAVIOR, IT IS
INAPPROPRIATE NO MATTER WHO IT
IS.
SHANNON: SOMETHING ON
CONVERSATION.COM THAT
ENCAPSULATES THIS CONVERSATION.
BIDEN'S ALLEGED CREEPINESS WAS A
TEST FOR ME TOO, IT PRESSES US
TO CONSIDER HOW WIDE WE WANT TO
CAST THE SAME NET.
SHOULD INCLUDE BEHAVIOR THAT IS
NOT OVERTLY SEXUAL?
IT DEMONSTRATES THAT GOAL IS■2AF
PO■s■s■2
T OF PY WE LIKEtO■O■■■■■■■■■■■■S
E HE HAPPE ON
OUR TEAM WE WI>■>■■■>■■■■■■■■■>
ER IT IS WHERE rEñ=N=■=■=ñ=■=■=8
ñ>ñ>OLUTELY, 1000%.■÷■÷>÷ñ÷■÷■÷÷
ñ÷BIGGEST REASON I D■÷TO
ON÷N÷N÷■÷ SAY SOMETHING WAS
BECAUSE TH■ PART OF
IS CONCERNED.HIS
THIS ISNST TIM
POINTEIATE
THEEN PICTURES,
ARTICLES WTHERE ARE
VIDEOS OF THIS WAS
■@■@■@ SOMETHING
a@■@ VERY WEp@p@■@p@Q@Q@■@■@■@■@
OFTEN TIMES IT WAS MADE
THAT'S JN BEING BIDEN.■@A@A@A@■■
ALL.
IT IS LITERALLY THE NEXT DAY HE
WA ABOUT IT ■@
TO TOUCH@@@@@@@@@@@@@@■@@@@@@@B
PERMISSION OR UNLESS IT IS
SOCIAL TOUCHING.
I'M NOT OUT THERE TRYING TO SAY
WE CAN'T GIVE FRIENDLY HUGS
ANYMORE AND WE CAN TOUCH ONE
ANOTHER WHEN TAKING PICTURES, OF
COURSE WE CAN.
THAT'S NOT WHAT WE ARE TALKING
ABOUT.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT AS WOMEN WE
HAVE HAD TO INDOOR THIS KIND OF
INAPPROPRIATE BEHAVIOR ON BEHALF
OF POWERFUL MEN FOR AS LONG AS I
HAVE BEEN ALIVE BUT FOREVER AND
WE HAVE GOTTEN TO THIS POINT
N SPEAK OUT
Y NO.
MAYB W
AUDN'T FEEL
D SAING BUT ■W WE CAN. IT FOR W.
SHANNON: YOU TORS
AND
THERE ARE MANY CRITICS.OUT THAT
YOU WERE A SUPPORTER BERNIE
SANDERS IN 2016, THEY QUESTION
YOUR POLITICAL MOTIVATION.
I WANT YOU TO RESPOND TO THAT.
>> IT IS ENTIRELY INAPPLICABLE.
THE REASON WHY WOMEN END UP
TALKING ABOUT THEIR EXPERIENCES
WITH POWERFUL MEN BEFORE THEY
ARE ABOUT TO BE CONFIRMED FOR
SOMETHING IS BECAUSE THAT IS
WHEN THE CONVERSATION BECOMES
WIDESPREAD.
THAT IS WHEN PEOPLE TALK ABOUT
AND START TO FIT THESE PEOPLE
FOR THE THI ARE TRYING
TO DO.
OBVIOUSLY IT IS APPLICABLE HERE
BECAUSE WE NEED TO HAVE THIS
CONVERSATION ABOUT HIS HISTORY.
>> WHAT YOU VOTE FOR HIM AS A
CANDIDATE?
>> I HAVE SAID MANY TIMES THAT
IN THE PRIMARY I WILL NOT BE
VOTING FOR HIM, I WILL NOT
SUPPORT HIM.
I HAVE MANY PROBLEMS BESIDES
THIS WITH SOME OF THE POSITIONS
HE HAS TAKEN IN THEA■
PAST BUT
TO MAKE THEIR ISION.I KNEW THIS
ASPECT OF HIS HISTORY THAT
NEEDED TO BE DISCUSSED BECAUSE
CONVERSATIWITH THIS  LIKE FOR N
AND WE WILL SEE WHERE IT GOEERE.
THANK YOU.
ANOTHER FORT, THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION SAYS IT IS
NG THE HAMMER ON IRAN'S
ABILITY TO GENERATE REVENUE
STARTING WITH THEIR BIG OIL
EXPORTS, TRACE GALLAGHER HAS
MORE.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE LONG SAID
IRAN'S NEFARIOUS ACTIVITIES ARE
DESTABILIZING SECURITY AND THE
US CAN LIMIT IRAN'S OIL EXPORTS
AND CUT OUT A MAJOR SOURCE OF
FUNDING AND CUT DOWN ON THE
VARIOUS ACTIVITIES SO THE
ADMINISTRATION WILL NOT RENEW
WAIVERS THAT ALLOWED EIGHT
COUNTRIES TO KEEP BUYING IRANIAN
CRUDE INCLUDING CHINA, TURKEY
AND INDIA, IRAN'S BIGGEST
CUSTOMER.
>> WE ARE GOING TO 0 ACROSS THE
BOARD.
WE WILL CONTINUE TO ENFORCE
SANCTIONS AND MONITOR
COMPLIANCE.
ANY ENTITY INTERACTING WITH THE
RANCH INTRODUCED DILIGENCE AND
AIR ON THE SIDE OF CAUTION.
>> Reporter: EVEN THOUGH MIKE
POMPEO SAID THE US IS GOING TO 0
HE ALSO WOULD NOT RULE OUT THE
POSSIBILITY OF LIMITED
EXCEPTIONS.
SINUSES IT OPPOSES US SANCTIONS
AND TURKEY CALLS THEM ILLEGAL.
>> POLITICALLY IT IS NOT RIGHT,
ETHICALLY IT IS NOT RIGHT.
IN TERMS OF COMMERCE IT IS
DEFINITELY NOT RIGHT AND IS ALSO
AGAINST INTERNATIONAL LAW OF
COMMERCE.
>> SOME BELIEVE LIMITING IRANIAN
EXPORTS COULD LEAD TO A SUPPLY
SHORTAGE AND PRICE INCREASE.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO NOTE THAT
VENEZUELAN IT OIL EXPORTS HAVE
BEEN TARGETED AND
LIBYA, ALSO
MAJOR EXPORTER, A BARREL OF OIL
IS NOW ABOVE $74, THE HIGHEST
PRICE IN 6 MONTHS AND AAA SAYS
CALIFORNIA GAS PRICES ARE THE
HIGHEST IN 5 YEARS THOUGH THAT
HAS A LOT MORE TO DO WITH STATE
POLITICS AND SANCTIONS AND IRAN
WILL CERTAINLY BE A CORE -- KEY
FOREIGN POLICIES ON THE 2020
CAMPAIGN.
6 DEMOCRAT PRESIDENT OF
CONTENDERS OF ALREADY SAID THEY
SUPPORT REENTERING THE IRAN
NUCLEAR DEAL.
JOE BIDEN WHO WAS VICE PRESIDENT
WHEN THE DEAL WAS SIGNED WILL
LIKELY BE THE SEVENTH.
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE AISLE
TEXAS GOP SENATOR JOHN CORNYN
SENT A LETTER TO DONALD TRUMP
SUPPORTING HIS MAXIMUM PRESSURE
SIGN■LICAN AINST IRAN.■■■
SENATORS.■■=■■==■==■■■■=■■■■■■■=
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.■■==■■■■■
NORTH KOREAN STATE MEDIA
ANNOUNCING RASHIDA TLAIB MEET
WITH VLADIMIR PUTIN.
DONALD TRUMP VISIT AL.■■w■■
BUCKINGHAM PALACE IN JUNE.
IN AN OFFICIAL STATE VISIT TO
THE UNITED KINGDOM THE
VISITATION WILL BE AS REQUIRED
BY PROTOCOL.
EASTER SUNDAY SHATTERED BY
TERRORISM, SOME UNWILLING TO
CALL IT A FAITH-BASED ATTACK.
WE TALK ABOUT CHR
PERSECUTION NEXT.
- In a CrossFit we're reald
with who we are as people and
verybody feel welcome.
Ordering Custom Ink T-shirts
has been a really smart
decision for our business.
I love the Custom Ink Design Lab
because it's really easy to use.
They have customer service
that you can reach anytime.
T-shirts help us immediately
get a sense of who
we are as a group.
From the moment clie?7?7?7?7
they're able to feel
like part of the family.
- [Spokesman] Custom Ink
has hundreds of products
for your business
and free shipping.
Upload your logo or
start your design today
at customink.com.
What kind of world do you
want to live in?
I want to bring pride
back to our communities.
I want people to wear
what they want.
I want us to be free
to talk about mental health.
I want humanity to reconnect
with nature.
I want sustainable to
be the solution
not the alternative.
Make the world you want.
You've got the power.
We've got the tools.
♪♪
>> ANOTHER EXPLOSION ROCKING THE
CAPITAL AFTER COORDINATED LAST
KILLED 290.■@
MONDAY'S EXPLOSION CAME AS POLI
VAN.
TWO PAK CHURCHES WERE TARGETED
EASTER SUNDAY LEAVING
BLOODSOAKED PEWS BUT SAINT
ANTHONY'S WHICH SUMMITS OF THE
CARNAGE FROZE AT THE TIME OF THE
ATTACK.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS
OFFERED ASSISTANCE.
>> I SPOKE WITH THE PRIME
MINISTER AND VARIOUS GOVERNMENT
OFFICIALS AND WE ARE WORKING
WITH SRI LANKA BUT THAT IS A
TERRIBLE THING.
>> TOURISTS WERE TARGETS, 31
FOREIGNERS DIED INCLUDING
SEVERAL AMERICANS INCLUDING A
FIFTH-GRADER FROM DC.
THE ATTACKS WERE CARRIED OUT BY
7 SUICIDE BOMBERS, LITTLE-KNOWN
GROUP.
SOON AFTER THE ATTACK POLICE
CARRIED OUT RAIDS ACROSS THE
CAPITAL.
OFFICIALS BELIEVE THE GROUP WAS
HELPED BY AND PERHAPS FUNDED BY
AN INTERNATIONAL TERROR NETWORK.
THE INTELLIGENCE SERVICES
RECEIVED A TIP OFTEN BEGIN AGO
FROM INTERNATIONAL AGENCIES, THE
SUICIDE BOMBER AT LATEST ATTACK.
>> CHRISTIAN AND CATHOLIC
URCHES AND TOURIST
DESTINATIONS.
>> Reporter: IT IS NOT KNOWN WHO
MAY HAVE LED THE ATTACKERS BUT
THEY FOUGHT WITH ISIS AND IRAQ
IN SYRIA.
THE SHOP WAS VISIBLE ACROSS THE
AREA AND THEY CAME TO TERMS WITH
E ATROCITY
THE COUNTRY IS I■
EMERGENCY IN SRI LANKA'S
PRESIDENT HAS GIVEN THE MILITARY
SWEEPING WARTIME POWERS.
THE US IS ISSUED A TRAVEL
ADVISORY WARNING THAT THERE
COULD -7■7■7■7SHHE■;■;■;■;o;o;■
REPORTEDLY RISEN TO 311.
WHAT ABOUT THOSE EARLY WARNINGS.
LET'S BRING IN THE OP-ED EDITOR
FROM THE YOUR POST AND BOB
SEXTON.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
READING SOMETHING FROM THE NEW
YORK TIMES, SRI LANKA WAS WARNED
OF POSSIBLE TAX, WHY DIDN'T IT
STOP THEM?
CONFIDENTIAL SECURITY MEMO LAID
IT ALL OUT, NAMES, ADDRESSES,
PHONE NUMBERS, THEY KNEW AS FAR
BACK AS JANUARY, THEY STOCKPILED
WEAPONS AND THAT IS NOT ALL.
HOW DOES THIS FAILURE HAPPEN?
>> A MASSIVE INTELLIGENCE
FAILURE.
THERE WILL BE A LOT OF
FINGER-POINTING AND THEY HAVE TO
DO ALL EFFORT TO FIGURE OUT WHY
THEY WOULD MESS SOMETHING UP
LIKE THIS WHEN THERE WERE A LOT
OF DETAILS BUT IT MIGHT BE
BECAUSE THE INTELLIGENCE
SERVICESi7■7■7 HAVEN'T BEEN LOOT
JIHADISTSS, THAT HASN'T BEEN A
THREAT.
THIS IS Y THAT UNTIL A
DECADE AGO WAS IN THE MIDST OF A
MULTI-DECADE-LONG CIVIL WAR BUT
PRIMARILY NATIONALIST IN
NATURE BETWEEN BUDDHIST AND
HINDUS.
THEY HAVEN'T HAD THIS JIHADIST
PROBLEM.
WHEN THAT INFORMATION CAME IN,
IT IS POSSIBLE THEY COULD MISS
SOMETHING WHERE THE ROADMAP WAS
SO DRAWN OUT, SOUNDS LIKE THEY
HAD CLEAR THREAT WARNING.
THEY ASSUMED IT MUST BE A THREAT
THAT IS EXAGGERATED BECAUSE THEY
HAVEN'T LOOKED AT THIS IN THE
PAST.
IT HASN'T HAD ITS FAIR SHARE OF
JIHADIST TERROR ATTACKS.
IT IS A QUESTION OF NOT BE
LEAVING THE THREAT WAS ACCURATE.
HEATHER: YOU HAVE A LOT MORE
INFORMATION, THIS IS A VERY
METICULOUSLY TO HAVE THESE NEAR
SIMULTANEOUSLY EXPLOSIONS AND
HELP FROM A MORE SOPHISTICATED
GROUP.
THE WALL STREET JOURNAL AND
EDITORIAL HEADLINE SAYS WORLD
LEADERS ARE DENOUNCING THE
ATTACK ON HUMANITY BUT MAKE NO
MISTAKE THIS WAS AN ATTACK ON
CHRISTIANS.
THE BOMBS WENT OFF IN PLACES OF
WORSHIP DURING SERVICES ON THE
HOLIEST DAY OF THE CHRISTIAN
CALENDAR.
>> THE EDITORIAL IS ABSOLUTELY
RIGHT.
WE HAVE THIS IDEOLOGY OF RADICAL
JIHADIST HIM IN VARIOUS
GEIC PERMUTATIONS AND
DIFFERENT STRANDS OF THE
ORGANIZATION ARE ALL DIFFERENT
BUT ONE THING THEY ALL SHARE IS
A HATRED OF CHRISTIANS THAT LIVE
IN THEIR MIDST, WHETHER IT BE IN
NIGERIA OR THE RAVAGES THAT HAS
BEEN ON CHRISTIAN VILLAGERS IN
NIGERIA WHETHER IT WAS IN LIBYA
OR EGYPT OR JORDAN AND ELSEWHERE
THAT IS ONE COMMON THREAD AND WE
HAVE TO CALL IT OUT.
ALSO IT IS A REMINDER THAT THE
ISLAMIC STATE LOST ITS
TERRITORIAL HOLD ON THE LAFOND
AND MESOPOTAMIA NEVERTHELESS THE
IDEOLOGY REMAINS SO WHATEVER
ISIS 2.0 IS TAKING SHAPE THIS
MIGHT BE THE BEGINNING OF THAT.
SHANNON: I WANT YOU TO COMMENT
ON THE US LIFTING WAIVERS ON
COUNTRIES THAT WANT TO BUY FROM
IRAN.
WE HAVE 5 REMAINING COUNTRIES IN
THE SPOTLIGHT.
CHINA COMES TO MIND IS ONE TO
WATCH FOR, TURKEY, QUICK COMMENT
ON HOW THIS WORKS OUT FOR IRAN
IN THOSE COUNTRIES.
>> THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IS
TRYING TO PUT WHAT WE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION GOT WRONG, NO
NEED TO SIGN A BAD DEAL AND GIVE
THE IRANIAN'S A LOT OF LEEWAY
PARTICULARLY ON THE FINANCIAL
SIDE OF THE EQUATION THAT THEY,
DID NOT EARN FROM REAL
CONCESSIONS, THEY GOT US OUT OF
THE DEAL AND SAY THEY ARE GOING
TO TAKE IT FURTHER, CHANGE
IRANIAN BEHAVIOR THAT IS
SERIOUS, THIS IS WHAT WE SHOULD
BE DOING.
>> I WOULD ADD IT IS AMAZING. T
ME WE STILL TALK ABOUT THIS
ADMINISTRATION IS SOMEHOW
BEHOLDEN TO MOSCOW
KREMLIN AND YET YOU HAVE ONE
MORE EVIDENCE HERE OF THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION SQUEEZING
RUSSIA'S MAIN MIDDLE EAST ALLY
IRAN. T
NOT BY ANY OF ITS POLICIES.
SHANNON: THANK YOU BOTH.
WHO COLLUDED WITH WHOM?
DEMOCRATS GET THIS INFORMATION
FROM THE RUSSIANS ON DONALD
TRUMP AND ARE THEY WILLING TO
DIG INTO THAT POSSIBILITY?
THAT IS NEXT.
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
♪♪
Applebee's Bigger, Bolder
Grill Combos.
Now that's Eatin Good
in the Neighborhood.
I had no symptoms
of Hepatitis C.
Mine...
çX @ @■■■■■
...caused liver damage.
EPCLUSA treats all main types
of chronic Hep C.
Whatever your type,
ask your doctor
if EPCLUSA is your kind of cure.
I had the common type.
Mine was rare.
EPCLUSA has a 98%
overall cure rate.
I just found out
about my hepatitis C.
I knew for years.
EPCLUSA is only one
pill, once a day,
taken with or without
food for 12 weeks.
Before starting EPCLUSA,
your doctor will
test if you have had
hepatitis B, which may flare up
and could cause
serious liver problems
during and after treatment.
Tell your doctor if you
have had hepatitis B
other liver or
kidney problems, HIV
or other medical conditions...
...and all medicin takcluding .
Taking amiodarone
with EPCLUSA may
cause a serious slowing
of your heart rate.
Common side effects include
headache and tiredness
Ask your doctor today, if
EPCLUSA is your kind of cure.
>> CALLS TO INATE THE
ORIGINS OF THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S
PROBE GETTING LOUDER FUELED BY
THE FACT THE MUELLER REPORT
FOUND SEVERAL ALLEGATIONS WERE
COMPLETELY FALSE OR IMPOSSIBLE
TO VERIFY.
THE NEW YORK TIMES RIGHT NOW THE
DOSSIER FINANCED BY HILLARY
CLINTON'S CAMPAIGN AND
DEMOCRATIC NATIONAL COMMITTEE
AND COMPILED BY THE FORMER
BRITISH INTELLIGENCE AGENCY IS
LIKELY TO FACE NEW SCRUTINY FRO■
MULTIPLE INQUIRIES.
FORMER DEPUTY ASSISTANT ATTORNEY
GENERAL HARRY LITTMAN AND JOHN
YOU, WELCOME TO BOTH OF YOU.
A LOT OF QUESTIONS.
THIS WEEKEND THE NEW YORK TIMES
WRITING A LOT OF THIS DIDN'T PAN
OUT, EITHER NOT TRUE, CAN'T
PROVE IT AND NOW THEY SOUND LIKE
CRITICS OF THE DOSSIER TWO YEARS
IN.
IF YOU READ THE FIRSME OF
ND LOOK FOR
COON OST
BE MUELLERONCLUDED
PRETTY WERE FALS
G OR NOT WORTH
LOOKING AT ARE FOLLOWING UP ON
SO THE QUESTION IN MY MIND IS
HOW WERE OUR INTELLIGENCE
AGENCIES, WERE THEY NAÏVE AND
GULLIBLE?
SOMETHING THEY SO BADLY WANTED
TO BELIEVE, THE TRUMP WAS
WORKING FOR THE RUSSIANS THAT
THEY PASSED IT ALONG TO THE FISA
COURT TO GET WARRANTS WITHOUT
SECOND GUESSING OR CHECKING IT
OR IS SOMETHING MORNING FARIAS
GOING ON?
WERE PEOPLE IN THE
ADMINISTRATION IN THE
INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES WANTING TO
STOP TRUMP, WHO WERE WORRIED
ABOUT HIM SO THEY BOUGHT THE
WHOLE THING HOOK, LINE AND
SINKER TO USE IT FOR A BAD
PURPOSE WHICH WAS SPYING ON
ONGOING PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN BY
A MAJOR PARTY?
>> A LOT OF FOLKS ARE ASKING
QUESTIONS ON SUNDAY SHOWS AND
TALKING ABOUT WHETHER THIS WAS
RUSSIA'S MOST BRILLIANT MOVE,
SPREADING DISINFORMATION, CHRIS
WALLACE, CHAIRMAN OF THE HOUSE
COMMITTEE, ADAM SCHIFF WAS ASKED
IF HE WOULD BE WILLING TO
INVESTIGATE THE DOSSIER ITSELF
AS TO WHETHER IT WAS RUSSIAN
THIS INFORMATION AND HERE'S HIS
RESPONSE.
>> THE MUELLER REPORT MAKES IT
ABSOLUTELY CRYSTAL CLEAR THAT
THE INITIATION OF THIS
INVESTIGATION WAS NOT ONLY
WARRANTED BUT ABSOLUTELY
NECESSARY BECAUSE IT REVEALED A
WIDESPREAD SYSTEMIC EFFORT BY
THE RUSSIANS TO HELP THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN.
SHANNON: SHOULD DEMOCRATS BE
WILLING TO SEE IF THAT INCLUDED
SPREADING DISINFORMATION THROUGH
THE DOSSIER?
>> MAYBE.
I KIND OF AGREE WITH JOHN.
THERE WERE SOME SNIPPETS HE
VERIFIED, OTHERS HE SAID WERE
WRONG.
ASSISTING WAS TWO THINGS, THE
QUALITY OF THE INFORMATION WE
GET, HOW WE KNOW IT IS THE BEST
IS ONE THING BUT SECOND THE MOST
THE ACTUALD BE
EVIDENCE OF THAT SO AS TO THE
SPYING POINT THAT THEY WERE
DUPED ON PURPOSE I JUST DON'T
THINK THERE IS ANY REASON TO
THINK IT BUT IT IS FINE TO LOOK
AND FIGURE OUT HOW IT IS THAT
SOME OF THE INTELLIGENCE WAS NOT
BORN OUT.
SHANNON: I WANT OTHER PEOPLE TO
COMMENT, NEW SUBPOENAS OF GONE
OUT, THE NEWEST TO DON MCGANN
AND THE BACK AND FORTH BETWEEN
THE PARTISANSHIP, REPUBLICANS
AND DEMOCRATS, OVER THIS.
CONGRESSMAN COLLINS SAYS THIS.
I ENCOURAGE YOU TO TAKE THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL UP ON HIS OFFER
TO READ THE FULL REPORT.
DISMISSING THIS OFFER AND
REFUSING TO REVIEW THE REPORT
YOU DEMANDED AS SOON AS POSSIBLE
ANNOUNCED A DERELICTION OF DUTY.
THE PRESIDENT IS FIGHTING
ANOTHER SUBPOENA IN COURT SAYING
HE WILL KEEP HIS FINANCIAL
RECORDS FROM BEING TURNED OVER.
>> THIS PUTS THE WHITE HOUSE IN
A TOUGH LEGAL SPOT BUT NOT OF
POLITICAL SPOT.
LEGALLY THEY COULD CLAIM
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE.
THE IDEA THE PRESIDENT'S
COMMUNICATION SHOULD BE
PROTECTED BY THE CONSTITUTION SO
HE CAN EFFECTIVELY PURSUE HIS
RESPONSIBILITIES HAS BEEN
RECOGNIZED BY COURT SINCE THE
WATERGATE TAPES CASE AND
PRACTICED FOR MANY■■■■■■■■ DECAS
BEFORE THAT BUT POLITICALLY THE
SMART THING WOULD BE FOR TRUMP
W■■■XECUTIVE PRIVILEGE,
LET DON MCGANN APPEAR IN■■■■
■■TELL T■■
WE HAVE HISTORIC, MUELLE
■■■■
ALMOST NO REDACTIONS AROUND IT.■
WHY NOMP POLITICALLY
WOMART TO LET ALL■■■■ THE
■■ATION OUT BECAUSE MUELLER
ALREADY HAS.
WHVERYTHING PRIVILEG■■■■■■■■■■D?
>> IT MAY BE THE WHITE HOUSE
DOES.
THE OTHER SUBPOENA THAT COMES
FROM CONGRESSMAN CUMMINGS, THE
CHAIRMAN, HE'S ASKING FOR
TOTALLY DIFFERENT THINGS, FINAC
PRESIDENT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THE LAWSUIT FROM FILED TODAY,
HOW ANOMALOUST WAS HE SUED
CUMMINGS PERSONALLY, SO THERE IS
NO LEGITIMATE OVERSIGHT.
IT IS IRONIC, HE CLAIMS IN THE
PAST YOU CAN'T SECOND-GUESS ME,
MY BROAD AREA OF AUTHORITY.
THAT'S RIGHT FOR CONGRESS TOO.
IT WILL BE HARD TO ASSERT AND I
DON'T THINK IT WILL WIN, THE
CONGRESS HAS NO LEGITIMATE
OVERSIGHT PURPOSE IN LOOKING FOR
THOSE RECORDS AND THAT'S THE WAY
IT WINDS UP.O■■■■■
HEATHER: THEY SAY IT IS ABOUT
EXPOSING THE PREO USE IT
AS A POLITICAL TOOL AGAINST HIM
IN 2020.
WE WILL SEE IF THE JUDGE BUYS
THAT.
THANK YOU BOTH VERY MUCH, GREAT
TO HAVE YOU.
50 MILES FROM BOSTON TONIGHT
BERNIE SANDERS SAYS EVEN THE
BOSTON MARATHON BOMBERS SHOULD
HAVE THE RIGHT TO VOTE.
>> YES, EVEN FOR TERRIBLE PEOPLE
BECAUSE ONCE YOU START CHIPPING
AWAY YOU ARE RUNNING DOWN A
SLIPPERY SLOPE.
>> OUR POLITICAL PANEL JOINS US
NEXT.
DOUG SHOWN, CHARLIE KIRK.
■■■ó=tL
>> IF ANY OTHER HUMAN BEING IN
THIS COUNTRY HAD DONE WHAT IS■■
REPORT, HE WOULD BE ARRESTED AND
PUT IN JAIL.
>> CONGRESS SHOULD TAKE A STEP
TOWARD IMPEACHMENT.
>> MULTIPLE TOWNHALL'S TONó
ó■■ó■ó■óó■óóóóóóó■óóó■óóó■■■
AND HARRIS■■■&s& JOINING THE COF
THOSE WHO SAY IT'S TIME TO THINK
ABOUT IMPEACHING THE PRESIDENT.
OR THE POWy=■=.
■=■=[=[=y=TER DOUG
SHOWN, TOINT USA FOUNDER
CHARLI[=■=■=[=[=■=[=■=■=■=■=■=■
CONTRIBUTOR CHARLIE HURTS,
WELCOME TO ALL OF YOU.
YOU KNOW THE DEMOCRATS ARE SPLIT
ABOUT THIS, THERE WERE PHONE
CALLS IN THE HOUSE, A NUMBER OF
HOUSE DEMOCRATS, BAST A
COUPLE OF THEM SEEM TO THINK IT
IS A WINNING STRATEGY.
>> THAT ISz=z=z=■=■=■=■=[=[=■=[
DEMOCRAT TO THE LEFT AND THERE
ARE 75% OF DEMOCRATIC PRIMARY
VOTERS SAYING IT IS RIGHT TO
IMPEACH TRUMP SO THAT IS WHAT IS
HAPPENING.
THE PROBLEM IS IT IS A
DISASTROUS GENERAL ELECTION
STRATEGY AS THE REPUBLICANS
FOUND IN 1998 AFTER THE
IMPEACHMENT OF BILL CLINTON SO
MY ADVICE TO MY FELLOW DEMOCRATS
pmROP THIS, MOVE ON, TALK
ABOUT ISSUES AND FORGET
IMPEACHMENT.
>> SPEAKING OF ISSUES BERNIE
SANDERS WAS ASKED ABOUT WHETHER
OR NOT SOMEONE LIKE THE BOSTON
MARATHON BOMBER SHOULD BE
ALLOWED TO VOTE FROM JAIL.
>> I THINK THE RIGHT TO VOTE IS
INHERENT TO OUR DEMOCRACY.
YES, EVEN FOR TERRIBLE PEOPLE.
ONCE YOU START CHIPPING AWAY
YOUR RUNNING DOWN THE SLIPPERY
SLOPE.
SHANNON: I SEE YOU SHAKING YOUR
HEAD.
>> OFTENTIMES WE ARE LOOKING FOR
EVIDENCE THAT A WAVE MIGHT BE
FORMING IN FAVOR OF ONE PARTY OR
ANOTHER PARTY.
THIS IS THE KIND OF MATERIAL YOU
START HEARING ABOUT WHERE YOU
START TO SEE A LANDSLIDE
FORMING.
THIS IS HOW DEMOCRATS MANAGED TO
DO SOMETHING LIKE LOSE ALL 50 y=
STATES, COME UP WITH CRAZY IDEAS
S IN THE PROBLEM FOR
DEMOCRATS IS BERNIE SANDERS IS
NOT SOME FRESHMAN IN THE HOUSE
WHO JUST ARRIVED IN WASHINGTON
AND IS POPPING OFF THE TOP OF
HIS HEAD WITH CRAZY IDEAS.
THIS IS THE GUY, THE ELDER
STATESMAN, PEOPLG FOR
THE NOMINATION, THE PERSON WHO
PROBABLY WOULD HAVE WON THE
NOMINATION IN 2016 IF IT HADN'T
BEEN TAKEN FROM HIM AND HAS A
GOOD SHOT AT BEING THE NOMINEE
THIS TIME.
CRAZY CRAZY IDEAS LIKE THIS ARE
WHAT TURNS OFF ALL THE
TRADITIONAL DEMOCRATIC STATES
THEY USUALLY RELY ON.
SHANNON: LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
UNIVERSITY OF NEW HAMPSHIRE
POLL, NEW HAMPSHIRE VOTERS AND
HERE'S HOW THEY RECORD, BERNIE
AT 30%, SECOND BIDEN, 18% EVEN
THOUGH HE'S NOT PARTICULARLY IN.
PETE BUTTIGIEG, WHAT DOES IT SAY
ABOUT THE FIELD?
WHITE GUYS.TORY AND YET THREE
>> BERNIE SANDERS WON NEW
HAMPSHIRE IN 2016, THERE'S
PROXIMITY TO HIS HOME STATE OF
VERMONT.
GOING BACK TO THE ABSURDITY OF
WHAT SENATOR SANDERS IS SAYING
HE GOES AND CRITICIZES THE
SECOND AMEUITE OFTEN IT
SAYS WE SHOULD INFRINGE ON THAT
RIGHT.
I'M NOT ABSOLU■2■2
DON'T THINK PEOPLE SHOULD HAVE
WEAPON ICE ARTILLERY.
YOU HAVE RESTRICTIONS.
A COMMON SENSE RESTRICTION WOULD
BESTS, SOMEONE CONVICTED
OF DOMESTIC TERRORISM AND MURDER
SHOULD■ ■  NOT BE ABTE IN
THE ELECTIONS.
THAT SHOULD BE SOMETHING 99% OF
ALL AMERICANS BELIEVE IN AND
DOUG WEE, A GREAT WAY TO
TURN PEOPLE OFF AND SENATOR
SANDERS@ GOES OUT OF HIS WAY TO
AN EASY LAP ANSWER, I DON'T
THINK TERRORISTS SHOULD HAVE TH=
RIGHT TO VOTE, MOVE ON.
THIS SHOULD BE SOMETHING THAT
NOW THE PERSON IN FIRST PLACE IN
NEW HAMPSHIRE THINK THE BOSTON
BOMBER, 80 OR 90 MILES AWAY
SHOULD BE ABLE TO VOTE IN
ELECTIONS, THANK YOU DEMOCRATS,
KEEP THE GIFT COMING IT STILL
QUITE EARLY.
SHANNON: IN THE NEW YORK TIMES,
SHOULD A WHITE MAN BE THE FACE
OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY IN 2020?
IS THE BIGGER GAMBLE TO RISK A
WHITE MAN AND DISAPPOINT THE
BASE OR NOMINATE A MINORITY
CANDIDATE A WOMAN WHO MIGHT
STRUGGLE TO CARRY PREDOMINATELY
WHITE SWING STATES LIKE
WISCONSIN, MICHIGAN AND
PENNSYLVANIA THAT BARACK OBAMA
AND DONALD TRUMP WON?
REACT TO THAT.
>> WE SHOULD NOMINATE THE BEST
PERSON.
AFTER THE PRIMARY AND CAUCUS
PROCESS, WE SHOULDN'T PLAY
IDENTITY POLITICS ABOUT WHETHER
THE NOMINATION IS A WHITE MALE
OR BLACK WOMAN OR SOMETHING
ELSE.
THAT BEING SAID I'M ALL FOR
DIVERSE CITY ON THE TICKET, THAT
IS GREAT BUT WHEN YOU HAVE
QUOTAS OR CHOOSE CANDIDATES
BASED ON GENDER OR RACE IT IS
DOOMED TO FAIL CONTRARY TO
AMERICAN VALUES.
>> THAT IS WHAT THE PARTIES
ENCOMPASSING, THIS TICKET WILL
BE DIFFERENT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
DOUG IS RIGHT.
BY DEFINITION THOSE PEOPLE WHO
VOTED FOR BARACK OBAMA AND
TURNED AROUND AND VOTED FOR
DONALD TRUMP DON'T CARE ABOUT
YOUR SKIN COLOR, THEY ARE
LISTENING TO YOUR IDEAS, THAT'S
ALL I CARE ABOUT.
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY ARE THE
ONLY PEOPLE LEFT ANYMORE TALKING
ABOUT SKIN COLOR, GENDER AND ALL
THIS WAS EVERYONE ELSE IS
TALKING IDEAS SO UNTIL THEY STOP
THAT NONSENSE AND GETS INTO
TALKING ABOUT IDEAS THEY ARE
NEVER GOING TO WIN OVER THOSE
PEOPLE ESPECIALLY PLAYING
IDENTITY POLITICS.
SHANNON: FINAL WORD TO YOU.
>> DOUG HIT IT ON THE HEAD.
THIS REPRESENTS HOW DEMOCRAT
PARTY USED TO BE, NOT HOW IT IS,
THE FACE OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
DEMANDS IDENTITY POLITICS AND
THEY WILL HAVE A COMPETITION OF
WHO CAN PLAY IDENTITY POLITICS
THE BEST AND UNREASONABLY ATTACK
JOE BIDEN AND BERNIE SANTOS OR
SOMETHING THEY CANNOT CONTROL.
IT SHOULD BE A BATTLE OF IDEAS,
NOT SKIN COLOR AND THE DEMOCRAT
PARTY, THE MAJORITY WILL FOCUS
ON THAT AND CHARLIE MADE A DECK
OF HOW THEY WERE ABLE TO VOTE
FOR DONALD TRUMP WHEN PREVIOUSLY
VOTING FOR BARACK OBAMA.
SHANNON: LOOK AT THAT.
IT IS A TRIFECTA, GREAT TO HAVE
YOU.
NEW YORK MAYOR BILL DIBLASIO
WANTS TO TG BITE OUT OF
THE BIG APPLE INCLUDING GREEN.
>> WE ARE GOING TO INTRODUCE
LEGISLATION TO BAN THE GLASS AND
STEEL SKYSCRAPERS.
Nooooo...
Quick, the Quicker Picker Upper!
Bounty picks up messes quicker
and is 2x more absorbent.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker
Upper.
♪ ♪
Plants capture CO2.
What if other kinds of plants
captured &■■■
If these industrial plants had
technology■;■;■;■;■;■
that captured carbon like trees
we could help lower emissions.
Carbon Capture is important
technology -
and experts agree.
That's why we're working on ways
to improve it.
So plants...
can be a little more...
like plants.■■■C■%%%
- In a CrossFit gym,
we're really engaged
with who we are as people and
body feel welcome.
Ordering Custom Ink T-shirts
has been a really smart
decision for our business.
I love the Custom Ink Design Lab
because it's really easy to use.
They have customer service
that you can reach anytime.
T-shirts help us immediately
get a sense of who
we are as a group.
From the moment clie?;n,
they're able to feel
like part of the family.
- [Spokesman] Custom Ink
has hundreds of products
for your business
and free shipping.
Upload your logo or
start your design today
at customink.com.
Upload your logo or
start your design today
♪
Audible members know
listening has the power
to change us make us better
parents,
better leaders, better people.
And there's no better place
to listen than Audible.
With Audible you get a credit
good for any audiobook and
exclusive fitness
and wellness programs.
And now, you'll also get two
Audible originals:
titles exclusively
produced for Audible.
Automatically roll
your credits over
to the next month if
you don't use them,
and if you don't like a book
just swap it for free.
Enjoy 100% ad free
listening in the car,
on your phone or
any connected device.
And when you switch a device
pick up right where
you left off.
With our commitment
free guarantee,
there's never been
a better time
to start listening
to Audible.
The most inspiring minds, the
most compelling stories,
the best place to listen.
To start your free
30-day trial,
GGGGG   text Listen12 to
500500 today.
♪
>> ON THIS EARTH DAY CLIMATE
ACTIVISTS TOOK OVER THE
UNIVERSAL STUDIOS GLOBE,
DEMANDING ACTION FROM NBC
UNIVERSAL.
IN THE■=■=■K MORE THAN 1000 PEO
WERE ARRESTED AND MASS CLIMATE j
CHANGE PROTESTS.
THE BIG APPLE ABOUT TO BECOME
THE GREEN APPLEEW PLAN.
BILL DIBLASIO SAYS THE CITY MAY
HAVE TO BAN STEEL AND GLASS
SKYSCRAPERS.
DAVIDSON SAYS THAT HE MIGHT GIVE
UP AND 2020 RACE.
>> NO QUESTION THIS IS THE
LARGEST FIELD OF PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES IN HISTORY AND IS
LIKELY TO GROW LARGER SOON.
>> I SUSPECT WE WILL HAVE JOE
BIDEN JUMPING IN TO BE THE 20TH
ANNOUNCED DEMOCRAT CHALLENGING
DONALD TRUMP.
WILL YOU BE LUCKY 21?
>> I LIKE THAT, LUCKY 21.
>> Reporter: BILL DIBLASIO SAT
DOWN WITH MSNBC AND TALKED A
LITTLE 2020.
>> ELECTION IN 2020.
AND ELECTION WE ARE NOT
DEFINITELY GOING TO WIN, DONALD
TRUMP CAN WIN.
>> TO CUBA THAT FROM HAPPENING
BILL DIBLASIO WANTS TO
FOCUS ON THE GREEN NEW DEAL,
CONCEPT INTRODUCEDANDRIA
OCASIO CORTEZ, EARLIER T
YEAR.F
HE SAYS TO TURN THE BIG APPLE
INTO THE GREEN APPLE WHICH HE
WANTS TO DO HE HAS BIG PLANS.
>> WE ARE GOING TO BAN THE
CLASSIC GLASS AND STEEL
SKYSCRAPERS WHICH ARE INCREDIBLY
INEF
IF SOMEONE WANTS TO BUILD ONE
THEY CAN TAKE A LOT OF STEPS■ T
MAKE IT ENERGY EFFICIENT BUT IT
WILL NOT BE LIKE IN THE PA
>> BILL DIBLASIO ANNOUNCING HIS
OWN GREEN NEW DEAL ON EARTH
THEY, CONSTRUCTING A BILL TO
TARGET THOSE SKYSCRAPERS.
>> THEY HAVE NO PLACE IN OUR
CITY OR EARTH ANYMORE.
IF A COMPANY WANTS TO BUILD A
BIG SKYSCRAPER THEY CAN USE A
LOT OF GLASS AND DO THE OTHER
THINGS NEEDED TO REDUCE
EMISSIONS.
>> SPEAKING OF EMISSIONS THE
MAYOR IS REALLY CRITICIZED FOR
TRAVELING 11 MILES TO THE GYM IN
AN SUV.
>> WHAT ENVIRONMENTALLY
RESPONSIBLE EXAMPLE ARE YOU
SITTING THERE?
>> IT IS PART OF MY LIFE.
I COME FROM THAT PART OF
OAKLAND, THAT IS MY HOME.
I GO THERE ON A REGULAR BASIS.
TO NOT BE IN THE BUBBLE FOR A
LOT OF POLITICIANS IS A HUGE
PROBLEM.
>> BILL DIBLASIO SAYS THE SUV IS
PART OF THE JOB.
HE WANTED BUILDINGS ARE NOT UP
BY 30% REDUCED EMISSION BY 2030
THE OWNERS OF THOSE BUILDINGS
COULD FACE MILLIONS OF DOLLARS
IN FINES WHICH HE WAS PRINCIPAL
A PRESIDENTIAL
ANNOUNCEMENT BUT SAYS HE'S
TALKING ABOUT OVER WITH HIS
FAMILY.
A HUGE RACE.
SHANNON: WOULD HE BE NUMBER 20?
WE ARE OFFICIALLY AT 19.
>> HE WOULD BE 20 PRESUMABLY.
JOE BIDEN IS 21.■]■
SHANNON: FOX NEWS ALERT, MEXICAN
POLICE DETAINING HUNDREDS OF
CENTRAL AMERICAN MIGRANTS AT THE
TAIL END OF THE CARAVAN
SUSPECTED TO BE MADE OF 3000
PEOPLE.
IT APPEARS TO BE THE LARGEST
RAID ON A CARAVAN SO FAR.
DONALD TRUMP RAMPING UP PRESSURE
ON MEXICO TO DO MORE TO CURB THE
■O■O APPING THE REAL IS RATHER.■
PATRICIA SEATON SA
HSOME TO HAVE A REPORTER BUT
ROBERT MUELLER AS HE WAS EXITING
CHURCH WITH HIS WIFE ON EASTER
SUNDAY.
SHE CHIDED THE NETWORK FOR
HAVING A, QUOTE, CHUCK
IT AFTERWARDS ADDING SHAME ON 8@
NEW ALLEGATIONS AGAINST STORMY
DANIELS ATTORNEY M
AVENATTI ACCUSED OF EMBEZZLING
$2■■MEANT FOR A FORMER■■■■■■■■
PROSECUTORS SAY HE HAD THE MONEY
OM HIS CLIENT AND USED IT TO
PURCHASE A SHARE IN A PRIVATE
JET.
STARBUCKS ADDING SOMETHING NEW.
BOXES■■■■■■■■■/■/■/
BATHROOMS.
THE COMPANY SAYS IT IS AN EFFORT
SAFET C NG TO CLEAN THE ■STARB
EMPLOYS A SINGLE LOCAT■=■■u■■■■■
STUCK BY NEEDLES IN A MONTH.■ ■
WASHINGTON BECOMING THE FIRST T/
HUMAN REMAINS.
THE CEO OF A COMPANY HOPING TO
b" SITE IN WASHINGTON SAYS
BODIES CAN BREAK DOWN INTO SOIL
AND 3 TO 7 WEEKSED
ONES DECIDE WHAT TO ■
SOIL.
GOVERNOR INSLEE SAID HE IS
REVIEWING THE BILL.
MORE NEWS NEXT.
♪ Goin' down the only road
I've ever known ♪
♪ Like a drifter I was-- ♪
♪ Born to walk alone! ♪
Keep goin' man!
You got it!
If you ride, you get it.
♪ Here I go again ♪
GEICO Motorcycle.
15 minutes could save you
15% or more.
[music playing]
(VO)
This is the Averys.
■This is the Averys trying the
hottest new bistro.
Wait...and the
hottest taqueria?
And the hottest...What are
those? Oh, pierogis?
And this i■■■erys
wondering if eating out
is eating into saving for
their first home.
This is JC...
(Team Member)
Welcome to Wells Fargo,
how may I help?
(VO)
Who's here to help with a free
Financial Health Conversation,
no strings attached.
This is the Averys with the
support they needed to get
back on track. Well done guys.
(Tea4@8@■@8@8@8@8@8@8@8@■)
This is Wells Fargo.
>> DRAMATIC RESCUE CURRENT
CAMERA, 20 WHEN-YEAR-OLDS
KAYAKING IN CALIFORNIA WHEN THEY
CAPSIZED IN CHILLY WATERS WHICH
WAS HOURS BEFORE A HIGHWAY
PATROL HELICOPTER FOUND THEM.
RESCUERS ARE CREDITING THEIR