>> NOT IN MY
@y@yHEY AREDOINç■y■■■y@y@y
SOMETHING■■■■D.@y
OND, IN CASE DID NOT@8@8@8@8@8@8
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU FOR INVITING US INTO
YOUR HONIGHT, THAT IS IT
FOR THESPECIAL REPORT."
FAIR, BALANCED, AND STILL■ ■
UNAFRAID.
"THE STORY" HOSTED BY
MARTHA MacCALLUM STARTS RIGHT
NOW.
DIDN'T REALLY GET THE SKUNK AND
THE COP, NEED MORE.■■■■■■■■■■■ N
HEAR THE GUY "THAT IS GOING TO
GO VIRAL" APPEARED TO BE TO SEE
YOU, MARTHA.
>> Martha: THANKS, BRET.
ALL RIGHT EVERYBODY, BREAKING
TONIGHT, MY EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW
WITH RUSH LIMBAUGH, WHO WAS WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP THIS WEEKEND AS
HE BEGINS TO MOVE PAST THE
MUELLER REPORT.
AND LOOK AHEAD.
AND NOW JOE BIDEN BELIEVES HE
CAN BEAT THE PRESIDENT IN A RACE
FOR THE WHITE HOUSE, REPORTEDLY
JUST DAYS FROM ENTERING INTO THE
RACE.
THE START LOOKING A LITTLE
ROCKY, THE DATE MAY BE A MOVING
TARGET.
WE WILL SPEAK TO SOMEONE LATER
IN THE SHOW WHO IS CLOSE TO HIS
CAMPAIGN.
GOOD EVENING EVERYONE, I
MARTHA MacCALLUM AND THIS IS
"THE STORY" ."
THE PRESIDENT TWEETING UP A
STORE, HERE IS THE LATEST ONE
FROM JUST MOMENTS AGO.
HE SAYS "YOU MEAN THE STOCK
MARKET HIT AN ALL-TIME RECORD
HIGH?
AND THEY ARE ACTUALLY TALKING
IMPEACHMENT?
WILL I EVER BE GIVEN CREDIT FOR
ANYTHING BY THE FAKE NEWS MEDIA
ARE RADICAL LIBERAL DAMS?
NO COLLUSION," JUST FOR GOOD
MEASURE AT AN EXCAVATION POINT.
HERE IS RUSH LIMBAUGH, HOST OF
"THE RUSH LIMBAUGH SHOW, RUSH,
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE, GREAT
TO SEE YOU THIS EVENING.
>> Rush: THANK YOU FOR HAVING
ME.
THIS IS A ONE HOUR ON FOX I
HAVEN'T DONE IN A WHILE, SO IT
IS GREAT TO BE HERE.
>> Martha: IT IS GREAT TO HAVE
YOU BACK.
I WANT TO START WITH JOE BIDEN,
YOU'VE SEEN HIM RUN FOR
PRESIDENT TWICE BEFORE, IN 1984
AND 1988.
WHAT VERSION OF JOE BIDEN DO YOU
THINK WE'RE GOING TO GET THIS
TIME, AND HOW DO YOU THINK YOU
WILL DO?
>> Rush: MARTHA, LET ME SAY, I
SIT HERE TONIGHT COME IN MY
PALATIAL EIB SOUTHERN COMMAND
STUDIO.
I REMAINED STUNNED AND AMAZEDDED
THAT THE DEMOCRAT PARTY AND THE
MEDIA DO NOT UNDERSTAND WHO
DONALD TRUMP IS.
THEY DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW HE
WON, THEY DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
HE IS GOING TO WIN BACK A
2020.
THEY DON'T UNDERSTAND THE PEOPLE
O VOTED FOR HIM OR WHY.
THEY HOLD ALL OF THAT IN
CONTEMPT.
HERE'S<■NG: JOE BIDEN IS
PROBABLY THE BEST CHANCE THEY'VE
GOT, AND HE DOESN'T HAVE A.Z■Z■?
AND■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■ñ■ñ■■
THEM A■■■■ BRONTOSAURUSLE OFñ■ñ■
IS FROMñ■ñ■ñ■ñ■ JURASSIC PARK, T
ISN'T GOING TO SIT WELL WITH THE
REST OF THE PARTY, WHICH HAS
GONE SO FAR LEFT.
I DON'T THINK, BIDEN IS PUTTING
OFFICE ANNOUNCEMENT, I DON'T HOW
BADLY HE REALLY WANTS THISDh■X■V
÷÷>z■zCE OF WINNING IT■÷■÷■÷■÷■í
>> Martha: ALL RIGHT, SPEAKING
OF THE OTHER FOLKS WHO ARE
RUNNING, LET'S LISTEN TO
ELIZABETH WARREN TALKING ABOUT
HER LEAVING 95% OF COLLEGE DEBT.
WATCH THIS.
>> WE ARE GOING TO ROLLBACK
STUDENT LOAN DEBT FOR ABOUT 95%
OF STUDENTS WHO HAVE IT.
AND PART TWO IS TO MAKE SURE
THAT WE NEVER GET IN THIS MESS
AGAIN ON STUDENT LOAN DEBT, AND
THAT IS TO MAKE COLLEGE
UNIVERSALLY AVAILABLE, WITH FREE
TUITION AND FEES.
>> Martha: SO THERE IS A LOT
OF FREE STUFF AND A LOT OF THESE
PLANS, MEDICARE FOR ALL, RUSH,
FREE COLLEGE TUITION, YOUR DATA
GOES AWAY.
THE PRESIDENT AND THE APPROVAL
NUMBERS ARE DOWN AROUND 35%.
IS HE VULNERABLE TO ALL OF THESE
PROMISES FROM ALL OF THESE
DEMOCRATS?
>> Rush: NO, THE POLLS RIGHT
NOW DON'T MEAN ANYTHING, MARTHA.
IS ANYONE A MEMBER OF THE POLL
TWO YEARS BEFORE 2016?
THEY ALL HAD HILLARY WINNING IN
A LANDSLIDE.
THERE IS WAY TOO MUCH THAT IS
GOING TO HAPPEN.
POCAHONTAS IS NOT GOING TO BE
THE NOMINEE.
THESE DEMOCRATS ARE ALL IN THE
PROCESS OF TRYING TO OUT-LEF
OR OUT-LIBERAL EACH OTHER, AND
THERE IN A CAN$a$a$a$a
GIVE AWAY THE MOST.
BUT WITH ELIZABETH WARREN,
FORGIVING COLLEGE LOANS,
FORGIVING■@■@■@x@x@■@■@■@ DEBT,D
PROMISING FREE COLLEGE, MEDICARE
FOR ALL, A GREEN NEW DEAL -- WHY
IS ANYBODY GOING TO■@D TO GO
TO COLLEGE, BEC■@■@■@
GOING TO NEED A JOB, BECAUSE
DEMOCRATS ARE GOING TO BE GIVEN
NO MIND GIVING EVERYONE A
UNIVERSAL BASIC INCOME CARED WHY
DOES ANY OF THIS MATTER?
NONE OF THIS IS REAL, NONE OF
THIS CAN HAPPEN.
THIS IS DISINFORMATION, AND IT
IS REALLY, I THINK IT IS AN
INDICATION OF JUST HOW LITTLE
THEY THINK OF THEIR OWN VOTERS.
THAT THEIR OWN VOTERS DON'T EVEN
WANT TO WORK.
THEY DON'T EVEN WANT TO ACHIEVE.
THEY DON'T EVEN WANT TO PURSUE
EXCELLENCE.
THEY JUST WANT TO HAVE THEIR
HANDS OUT AND VOTE FOR WHOEVER
IS GOING TO GIVE THEM THE MOST.
WHAT A WAY TO RUIN A LIFE.
NO ONE WOULD RAISE KIDS THIS
WAY.
WHY IN THE WORLD HE DOES A
DEMOCRAT PARTY THINK -- I CAN
ANSWER THAT TOO -- SOMETIMES THE
BEST QUESTIONS ARE GET ARE THOSE
I CAN ANSWER MYSELF THERE THEY
CAN'T WIN ON POLICY.
THEY CAN'T WIN ON ANYTHING OF
SUBSTANCE, SO THEY HAVE TO
DEMONIZE, THEY HAVE TO
CRITICIZE, THEY HAVE TO IMPUGN
AND DESTROY THE CREDIBILITY OF
ALL OF YOUR OPPONENTS, AND THEN
PROMISED TO GIVE EVERYTHING
AWAY, PROMISE TO BE SANTA CLAUS.
IT'S NOT GOING TO WORK AGAINST
BEFORE.
IT MIGHT WORK AGAINST ROMNEY OR
A TRADITIONAL REPUBLICAN, BUT IT
WON'T WORK AGAINST DONALD TRUMP.
>> Martha: LET ME ASK YOU THIS
THEN, BECAUSE IT SEEMS THAT WHEN
YOU GO TO HIGH SCHOOLS AND
COLLEGE CAMPUSES, AND EVEN IN
HOLLYWOOD AND OTHER PLACES, THAT
DEMOCRATS HAVE WON THE ARGUMENT,
TO A CERTAIN EXTENT.
THERE IS A FEELING THIS COUNTRY
AMONG A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT THIS
IS THE WAY WE SHOULD LIVE.
IT REALLY BREAKS DOWN THE
COUNTRY IN TERMS OF THOSE WHO
THINK THAT WE SHOULD BE GIVING
ALL OF THESE THINGS, AND THE
PEOPLE WHO ARE TRUMP SUPPORTERS.
>> Rush: MARTHA, IF YOU WOULD
GO TO THE PLACES IN THIS COUNTRY
THAT ARE NOT ON THE COAST, NOT
IN THE ELITE, BIG URBAN AREAS
THERE AND GO TO THE AREAS
DONALD TRUMP WON THE ELECTION,
TRADITIONAL DEMOCRAT, WHITE,
BLUE-COLLAR NEIGHBORHOOD, YOU'RE
NOT GOING TO FIND THAT ATTITUDE.
THESE ARE THE PEOPLE DEMOCRATS
USED TO RELY ON.
THEY'RE THE PEOPLE THE DEMOCRATS
HAVE LOST.
THESE ARE THE PEOPLE THAT VOTE
FOR TRUMP, AND THEY LOVE TRUMP
EVEN MORE THAN THEY DID IN 2016.
THE MAJORITY OF THIS COUNTRY IS
NOT YET AT THE PLACE WHERE IT
WANTS EVERYTHING GIVEN TO THEM.
OF COURSE YOUNG PEOPLE WANT
THINGS GIVEN TO THEM.
KIDS ALWAYS DO.
PEOPLE THAT ARE NOT YET MATURE
COME HAVEN'T LIVED ENOUGH, BUT
WE ARE DOING A GREAT DISSERVICE
TO OUR KIDS BY SHORTCHANGING
THEIR HUMANITY, SHORTCHANGING
THEIR OPPORTUNITIES TO EXCEL, TO
BECOME SOMETHING, TO BECOME
LARGER THAN THEMSELVES.
THEY ARE NOTHING MORE THAN PONDS
THAT CAN BE BOUGHT WITH VOTES,
AND I DON'T THINK THERE IS A
MAJORITY OF OUR POPULATION -- UP
AGAINST DONALD TRUMP IS THE KEY
ELEMENT HERE.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S A MAJORITY
OF THE POPULATION THAT IS
SERIOUS ABOUT THINKING THIS IS
THE WAY THE COUNTRY OUGHT TO BE
RUN.
THE STUDENT LOAN FORGIVENESS,
WHAT ABOUT PEOPLE WHO TOOK LOANS
AND PAY THEM BACK?
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO, GIVE
THEM REPARATIONS?
ARE THEY GOING TO ASK FOR
REFUNDS?
WHERE DOES ALL OF THIS STOP?
IT ISN'T GOING TO HAPPEN IN THE
FIRST PLACE.
ALL OF THIS IS DISINGENUOUS, AND
DISHONEST.
AND IT DOESN'T GET ANYWHERE NEAR
THE HEART OF THE PROBLEMS THAT
WE ARE HAVING IN THIS COUNTRY,
WHICH I HAPPEN TO THINK REVOLVE
AROUND THE DISSIPATION OF OUR
CULTURE, THE DISSOLUTION OF OUR
SOCIETY, AND SO FORTH, AND THEY
ARE THE CULPRITS FOR THIS, AND
THEY NEED TO BE STOPPED.
THIS KIND OF STUFF IS NOT THE
ROUTE BACK.
AND THE FACT THEY ARE TALKING
ABOUT JOE BIDEN OR KRAZY BERNIE,
WHO IS LEADING EVERYBODY AT
THE STAGE, IT IS A TESTAMENT TO
HOW BANKRUPT THEY ACTUALLY ARE.
>> Martha: I WANT TO PLAY
SOMETHING FOR YOU FROM
HILLARY CLINTON, THE TIME 100
CONFERENCE SHE WAS AT, WHERE SHE
SAYS -- I KNOW HOW MUCH YOU LOVE
THE TIME 100 CONFERENCE AND
HOW MUCH YOU LOVE
HILLARY CLINTON, SO HERE SHE IS
TALKING ABOUT WHY SHE BELIEVES
PRESIDENT TRUMP SHOULD BE
INDICTED.
LISTEN TO THIS.
>> THERE IS ENOUGH THERE THAT
ANY OTHER PERSON WHO HAS ENGAGED
IN THOSE ACTS WOULD CERTAINLY
HAVE BEEN INDICTED.
THE WHOLE MATTER OF OBSTRUCTION
WAS VERY DIRECTLY SENT TO THE
CONGRESS.
IF YOU READ THAT PART OF THE
REPORT, IT COULD NOT BE CLEARER.
>> Martha: WHAT IS GOING
THROUGH YOUR MIND AS YOU ARE
LISTENING TO THAT, RUSH?
>> Rush: I WAS TRYING NOT TO
LISTEN TO THAT.
THIS IS THE IRONY.
HILLARY CLINTON IS WHO TRIED TO
RAKE A PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION,
MARTHA.
HILLARY CLINTON AND HER PALS IN
THE OBAMA DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE
AND THE FBI, THEY ARE THE ONES
WHO COLLUDED WITH THE RUSSIANS.
THEY ARE THE ONE THAT GAVE US
THIS ENTIRELY, TOTALLY BOGUS
STEELE DOSSIER.
CAN YOU THINK ABOUT IRONY?
FOUR HILLARY CLINTON TO BE
DONALD TRUMP, HILLARY CLINTON
TO BE INVESTIGATED, SHEñ■ñ■ñ■ñ.
MANY OF HER■÷ T■÷r■S IN■@@@
AM TO NOTHING■■■■■■■■■N A
■@@@P> OVERCURRENT             E
ELECTION RESULTS IN 2016 -- YOU
TALK ABOUT SOUR GRAPES.
THIS IS A WOMAN WHO HAS BEEN
REJECTED BY THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
TWICE, REJECTED BY HER PARTY IN
2008.
SHE HAD TO RIG THE PRIMARIES
AGAINST KRAZY BERNIE IN 2016 TO
GET THE NOMINATION.
SHE IS THE LAST PERSON WHO OUGHT
TO BE LISTENED TO ABOUT WHAT
OUGHT TO HAPPEN TO DONALD TRUMP.
SHE HASN'T ACCOMPLISHED ANYTHING
ANYWHERE NEAR WHAT DONALD TRUMP
HAS ACCOMPLISHED.
SHE IS IN NO POSITION TO SIT
HERE AND SAY WHAT SHE SAW IN THE
MUELLER REPORT -- WELL, SHE CAN
SAY BECAUSE SHE'S AN AMERICAN,
BUT SHE DOESN'T HAVE CREDIBILITY
ON ANY OF THIS AS FAR AS I'M
CONCERNED, AND I'M NOT ALONE.
>> Martha: JARED KUSHNER ALSO
SPOKE AT THE CONFERENCE TODAY,
AND I KNOW YOU TALKED ABOUT THIS
TODAY, HERE HE IS TALKING ABOUT
THE RUSSIANS ACTUALLY DID ON
FACEBOOK.
YEAH, LET'S PLAY■
>> INVESTIGATIONS AND ALL OF
THE SPECULATION THAT HAPPENED
THE LAST TWO YEARS HAS HAD A
MUCH HARSHER IMPACT ON THE
DEMOCRACY THAN A COUPLE OF
FACEBOOK ADS.
THEY SPENT ABOUT $160,000, I
SPEND $160,000 ON FACEBOOK EVERY
THREE HOURS IN THE CAMPAIGN
PURITY LOOK AT THE MAGNITUDE OF
WHAT THEY DID ON WHAT THEY
ACCOMPLISHED, I THINK THE
PURSUING INVESTIGATIONS HAVE
BEEN WAY MORE HARMFUL.
>> Martha: VERY INTERESTING TO
HEAR FROM HIM TODAY ON THAT AND
A LOT OF OTHER THINGS, RUSH.
>> Rush: WELL, HERE'S THE
THING.
HE'S RIGHT, MARTHA.
EVERYBODY, AMERICA, PLEASE,
THERE WAS NEVER ANY EVIDENCE OF
COLLUSION BETWEEN TRUMP AND
RUSSIA.
THE COLLUSION, AS I SAID, WAS
HILLARY, THE DNC, AND THE
RUSSIANS VIA STEELE.
BUT THE RUSSIANS -- WHEN MUELLER
ANNOUNCED THE INDICTMENT OF THE
RUSSIAN TROLL FARM, ROSENSTEIN
WITHOUT AN ANNOUNCEMENT, NOBODY
PAID ATTENTION TO THIS, BUT THE
END OF THE ANNOUNCEMENT, NOTHING
IN THESE INDICTMENTS SUGGEST A
SINGLE VOTE WAS CHANGED.
NOTHING SUGGESTS THE OUTCOME OF
ANY ELECTION WAS CHANGED.
NO AMERICAN IS NAMED IN THE
INDICTMENT HAVING TO DO WITH IT.
THERE WAS NEVER ANY EVIDENCE FOR
THIS.
THERE WAS NEVER MUELLER -- WHEN
HE GOT THE FILE FROM COMEY, IT
WAS EMPTY.
ALL THEY HAD WAS THE DOSSIER,
AND WE ALL KNOW THAT IT WAS MADE
UP.
IT WAS OPPOSITION RESEARCH.
THIS WAS NOT EVEN AN
INVESTIGATION OF TRUMP.
WHAT IT ONCE WAS AN ATTEMPT TO
OVERTHROW THE 2016 ELECTIONS,
AND THE MUELLER INVESTIGATION, I
BELIEVE, WAS ACTUALLY MANY
THINGS, INCLUDING A COVER-UP AND
A DISTRACTION TO KEEP PEOPLE
FROM UNDERSTANDING WHAT REALLY
HAPPENED.
DONALD TRUMP ACCOMPLISHED ONE OF
THE GREATEST ACHIEVEMENTS OF HIS
LIFE AGAINST ALL ODDS, WITH NO
ASSISTANCE.
HIS OWN PARTY WASN'T EVEN THAT
MUCH BEHIND HIM.
HE HAS DONE SOMETHING THAT FEW
AMERICANS WILL EVER DO, AND THEY
ARE TRYING TO TAKE IT AWAY FROM
HIM, AND THEY ARE TRYING TO
SULLY HIS REPUTATION, SIMPLY
BECAUSE THEY DON'T LIKE HIM.
THIS IS A SORDID SITUATION.
I THINK OUR COUNTRY WAS AT GREAT
RISK DURING THIS WHOLE THING.
AND THERE NEEDS TO BE AN
INVESTIGATION.
I HOPE THE ATTORNEY GENERAL IS
SERIOUS, BECAUSE THESE PEOPLE
NEED TO BE INVESTIGATED.
WE NEED TO BE TOLD WHO THEY ARE,
WHAT THEY DID, EVEN THOUGH WE
ALREADY KNOW.
AND THEY NEED TO BE INDICTED.
>> Martha: YOU SAY THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL IS ON IT.
>> Rush: BECAUSE THEY CAME
CLOSE, MARTHA, TO THROWING AWAY
THE UNITED STATES CONSTITUTION.
UNELECTED PEOPLE CAME CLOSE TO
ACTUALLY PULLING OFF WHAT IS A
COUP       ,
AND IT SHOULD NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN
FOR THE AMERICAN PEOPLE, THOSE
THAT WATCH CNN DON'T KNOW IT,
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" IS TRYING
TO BACK OFF THE DOSSIER NOW.
"WELL, MAYBE IT WAS RUSSIA" --
NO KIDDING.
THEY'VE KNOWN THAT FOR A YEAR
AND A HALF.
EVERYONE IN THE MEDIA HAS NO MAY
HAVE BEEN LYING TO THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE ABOUT THIS IN AN EFFORT
TO GET RID OF TRUMP APPEARED HE
SURVIVED IT, AND IF THEY THINK
THEY'RE GOING TO TAKE THEM OUT
AFTER ALL OF THIS, THEY ARE
DELUSIONAL.
>> Martha: AS YOU SAY,
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" IS NOW
LOOKING INTO THE DOSSIER.
THEY SAY THAT MR. STEELE'S
RUSSIAN INFORMANTS COULD HAVE
BEEN PRESSURED TO FEED HIM
DISINFORMATION, WHICH IS
SOMETHING WE REPORTED SOME TIME
AGO.
>> Rush: COLLUSION!
WAS WORKING WITH RUSSIANS?
STEELE, HILLARY CLINTON'S GUY.
BOB WOODWARD SAID THE OTHER
DAY -- HE'S TRYING TO LINK THE
DOSSIER TO PUTIN, NOT HILLARY!
THE DOSSIER TRACES RIGHT BACK TO
HILLARY AND HER CAMPAIGN WITH
THE DNC.
>> Martha: THEY PAID FOR IT,
AND THAT IS    MUCH WE KNOW.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT A PIECE
TODAY, THE FORMER PRESS
SECRETARY FOR BILL CLINTON.
HE TALKED ABOUT GOING DOWN THE
IMPEACHMENT ROAD, WE DON'T NEED
TO GO DOWN THE IMPEACHMENT ROAD
BECAUSE IT IS GOING TO BE GOOD
ENOUGH FATHER AS WE MOVE FORWARD
THAT THE PRESIDENT WILL BE UNDER
CONTINUED CONSTANT
INVESTIGATION.
ALL OF THESE SUBPOENAS ARE OUT
THERE.
BUT HERE'S WHAT HE SAID ABOUT
YOU, RUSH.
HE SAID PUBLICANS TODAY ARE THE
PARTY OF RUSH LIMBAUGH,
SEAN HANNITY, TUCKER CARLSON, A
COALITION IN THE FACE OF EVERY
DEMOGRAPHIC TREND IN AMERICA
WILL MEAN THE LONG-TERM
REALIGNMENT OF THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT BEHIND THE DEMOCRATS.
WHAT SAY YOU, SIR?
>> Rush: I'M HONORED THEY
THINK THIS.
SOME DAYS I'M JUST AN
ENTERTAINER.
SOME DAYS I'M A HAS-BEEN.
NOW I'M THE FACE OF AND THE
REASON FOR THE REPUBLICAN PARTY.
I THINK THAT ALL OF THIS JUST
ADDS UP THE FACT THAT THEY ARE
FRUSTRATED.
THEY HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO QUOTE
UNQUOTE DEFEAT ME IN 30 YEARS.
THEY CAN'T DEFEAT TRUMP COME
HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO STOP HIM,
AND I THINK THEY ARE FRUSTRATED.
THEY HAVE THROWN EVERY WEAPON
THEY HAVE IN THEIR ARSENAL AT
HIM, AND IT HASN'T WORKED FOR
THINGS THEY'VE USED OVER THE
YEARS THAT HAVE BEEN READILY
AVAILABLE TO GET RID OF AND TAKE
OUT ANY REPUBLICAN THEY WANT,
THEY HAVE BOUNCED OFF OF TRUMP.
AND I THINK THEY ARE REALLY
FRUSTRATED.
RUSH LIMBAUGH, SEAN HANNITY,
TUCKER CARLSON, WE ARE NOT IN
POLITICS.
WE ARE MEDIA TITANS, BUT WE ARE
NOT IN POLITICS.
IT IS THE PARTY OF DONALD TRUMP
RIGHT NOW, AND THE REPUBLICANS
THAT DON'T REALIZE THAT HAD
BETTER GET ON BOARD.
>> Martha: THAT'S INTERESTING,
BECAUSE I KNOW YOU SAID YOU ARE
FRUSTRATED BY OTHER REPUBLICANS
IN YOUR PARTY, WHO YOU FEEL
SHOULD BE REJOICING RIGHT NOW,
SHOULD BE FUND-RAISING OFF OF
THIS MUELLER REPORT FINDING.
YOU DON'T THINK THEY ARE DOING
THAT.
>> Rush: I THOUGHT IT WAS
STRANGE, FOR TWO YEARS, EVERYONE
IS WAITING WITH BAITED BREATH
AND BITING THEIR FINGERNAILS,
WHAT IS MULLER GOING TO DO?
AND THEN HERE COMES THE NEWS, NO
COLLUSION, NO OBSTRUCTION.
WHERE'S THE REPUBLICAN PARTY
WITH THE CELEBRATORY EMAILS TO
THEIR VOTERS?
EVEN FUND-RAISING, OR JUST
CELEBRATING THE VICTORY, WHERE
ARE THEY?
YOU DON'T HEAR THEM.
THE REASON IS, MARTHA, BECAUSE
THIS IS A BATTLE NOT BETWEEN TWO
PARTIES, THIS IS A BATTLE
BETWEEN THE WASHINGTON
ESTABLISHMENT AND THE
DEEP STATE, I CALL THEM THE
ADMINISTRATIVE STATE, AT
OUTSIDERS AND AMERICANS WHO FEEL
DISENFRANCHISED OR UNATTACHED.
THE FACT THAT THE REPUBLICAN
PARTY, THERE ARE STILL MANY
PEOPLE IN THEIR -- LIKE
MITT ROMNEY, SAYS HE WAS SICK
AND?
HE WAS SICKENED?
BY WHAT HE READ IN THE MUELLER
REPORT?
THIS IS THE SAME GUY,
MITT ROMNEY, WHO THEY SAID
DIDN'T CARE WHAT AN EMPLOYEE'S
WIFE DIED OF CANCER.
THE SAME GUY THEY SAID DIDN'T
PAY HIS TAXES FOR TEN YEARS.
THE SAME GUY WHO THEY SAID BEAT
UP SOMEBODY IN PREP SCHOOL.
THE SAME GUY WHO SAID HE HAD A
FILE OF NOTHING BUT WOMEN.
THEY DESTROYED MITT ROMNEY, AND
HERE HE IS, ON THEIR SIDE.
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU?
IT'S STRANGE, AND I THINK THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY, I KNOW THE
FIRST NINE MONTHS OF TRUMP'S
TERM, THEY THOUGHT THE RUSSIAN
STOCK WAS REAL, AFRAID TO GET
BEHIND IT.
THAT IS GONE, AND THERE IS NO
REASON TO GET
NO REASON NOT TO GET BEHIND HIM,
UNLESS YOU DON'T LIKE HIS
VOTERS, AND I THINK THAT IS KEY.
>> Martha: I SAW PICTURES OF
THE WEEKEND, YOU PLAYED GOLF
WITH THE PRESIDENT ON
EASTER SUNDAY.
EVERYBODY WOULD LIKE TO HEAR A
LITTLE BIT, WHAT HIS MOOD WAS
REALLY LIKE AND WHAT HE WANTS TO
FOCUS ON NOW■■■■■■■■ñ■ñsñsñs--
>> Rush: ACTUALLY, IT WAS
FRIDAY, THE DAY AFTER THE
MUELLER REPORT CAME OUT, AND
IS JUSñ■ñ■ SHE IS Añ■ñ■ñ■ñ■
PRO, AND WHEN WE SHOWED UP,
THERE IS NO WAY I AM IN TRUMP'S
CART, NOT WITH LEXI THOMPSON IN
E GROUP, BUT Iñsñpñ■ TRUMP'S
ñpWN.
GROUP, INCLUDING THOSE FROM THE■
PGA TOUR.
FOR THOSE WHO WOULD LIKE TO MEET
DONALD TRUMP, I TELLñ■ñ■ñ■
EVERYTHING YOU WOULD HOPE HE
WOULD BE.
HE MAKES EVERYBODY THEñ■■p■pfpfp
HE IS A TREMfp■p■pfpfp HOS■p■p■p
■p■p■p■pñ■ñ■■pfpfpfp■pfp■pfp■pfp
ñp■pfpñp■p■p■pñp■p■pHAT IS BETT■
BEACH, EVERYBODY KNOWS IT.
HIT THE BALL WELL.WHEN YOU DON'T
HE MAKESVERYBODY HAVE A
ñ■TIME, AND IT FEATURES BREAKFA
DS.
THERE'S NOñ■ñ■ñ■ñ■ñ■ñ■ LOT --
>> Martha: DID YOU WIN?ñp■p■p■p-
>>ñuñuñuñuñuñuñuñuñuñuñuñuñuñuñu
AS THE HARDESTN SO
FAR!
STROKES ON THE
USE ñpIDN'TñpñpñpESERVEE
SAID, I WAS P- DID I
MISUNDER■zUR QUESTION?
>> Martha: NO, THAT IS MY
QUESTION, I WANTED TO KNOW IF
YOU WON.
>> Rush: OH!
I WAS ON HIS TEAM.
HE PICKS WHOEVER IS PLAYING THE
BASS AND PUTS HIMSELF ON THEIR
TEAM.
HE MAY CHANGE TEAMS TO ARCO OR
THREE TIMES IN A ROUND.
IT IS JUST FUN, MARTHA.
>> Martha: I CAN TELL.
>> Rush: PLAYING TEAMS AGAINST
EACH OTHER, IT IS A FAUX
COMPETITION, BUT IT IS JUST FUN.
IF SOMEBODY HITS A BAD SHOT, HE
TELLS THEM, DROP ANOTHER BALL,
WHERE YOU'RE HAVING FUN.
>> Martha: EVERYONE IS HAVING
FUN.
LET ME ASK YOU ONE LAST
QUESTION.
I'M CURIOUS, WHEN YOU ARE WITH
HIM, IF YOU FELT THAT ANY OF THE
STOP IS WEIGHING ON HIM.
I KNOW ELIJAH CUMMINGS WANTING
TO DIG INTO EIGHT YEARS OF
FINANCIAL RECORDS IS SOMETHING
THAT SOME IN THE TRUMP CAMP ARE
NOT HAPPY ABOUT, AND THEY'RE
PUSHING BACK ON HARD BEER DID
THAT COME UP AT ALL?
>> Rush: P -- TO ME, AND
AROUND ME, HE IS ONE OF THE
MOST CONFIDENT PEOPLE, HE TALKS
ABOUT THIS STUFF, BUT HE DOES
NOT, AT ANY MOMENT, EXPRESS ANY
CONCERN.
CERTAINLY NO FEAR.
HE IS REASSURING.
HE KNOWS WHO HE IS, HE KNOWS HOW
PEOPLE SEE HIM, HE KNOWS HE IS
THE PRESIDENT, HE KNOWS PEOPLE
ARE RELUCTANT TO SPEAK, THEY
WILL BE RESPECTFUL.
AND SO HE ANTICIPATES THINGS
THEY ARE THINKING OR WONDERING
ABOUT, AND HE WILL PROVIDE
ANSWERS TO THINGS.
BUT MOSTLY, HE DIDN'T HAVE ANY
TIME SIT DOWN AND TELL ME WHAT
HE THOUGHT OF MUELLER OR WHAT HE
THOUGHT OF THIS OR THAT, HE
DOESN'T -- HE CAN'T TELL WHO IS
GOING TO SPEAK AND WHO ISN'T,
BUT THAT WOULDN'T GO ALONG WITH
THE RECIPE FOR THESE THINGS,
WHICH IS FUN.
BUT HE DOESN'T HIDE FROM ANY OF
THIS.
I WOULD LUNCH AFTER THE ROUND,
HE WAS TELLING LEXI ABOUT THE
GOLDEN SHOWERS STORY AND HOW
RIDICULOUS IT IS, AND EVERYONE
WAS LAUGHING -- THE FACT THAT
THE MEDIA BELIEVED IT.
THE FACT THAT PEOPLE ACTUALLY
THOUGHT THAT TRUMP WOULD HIRE
SOME PROSTITUTES TO URINATE ON A
BED OBAMA HAD SLEPT -- WE'RE
LAUGHING OURSELVES SILLY.
>> Martha: GREAT TO TALK TO
YOU, THANKS FOR SPENDING SO MUCH
TIME WITH US.
GREAT TO SEE YOU, SIR.
>> Rush: THANK YOU, MARTHA
APPEARED MARTHA.
>> Martha: YOU BACK.
ANDY McCARTHY IS COMING UP
NEXT.
MORE OF "THE STORY" AFTER THIS.
■
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it
from your allergy pills?
Flonase relieves
your worst symptoms
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
Flonase helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances.
Most pills only block one.
Flonase.
♪ LiMu Emu & Doug ♪
What do all these people
have in common, Limu?
[ paper rustling ]
Exactly, nothing.
They're completely
different people,
that's why they
need customized
Car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need!
[ gargling ]
[ coins hitting the desk ]
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done
it again, LiMu.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
xxx
There's brushing...and
there's Oral-B Power brushing.
Oral-B just cleans better.
Even my hygienist said
going electric could lead to way
cleaner teeth.
And unlike Sonicare,
Oral-B is the first electric
toothbrush brand
accepted by the ADA.
Oral-B.
Brush like a pro.
♪ ♪
>> I'M REALLY OF THE MIND THAT
THE MUELLER REPORT IS PART OF
THE BEGINNING.
IT'S NOT THE END.
MAYBE, AS CHURCHILL'S FAMOUSLY
SAID, THE END OF THE BEGINNING,
BECAUSE THERE IS STILL SO MUCH
MORE THAT WE SHOULD KNOW AND ACT
UPON.
OBVIOUSLY, THAT IS WHAT THE
CONGRESS IS TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO DO RIGHT NOW.
>> Martha: HILLARY CLINTON
ECHOING THE CALLS FOR OTHER
DEMOCRATS TO WANT TO KEEP THE
INVESTIGATIONS GOING INTO
PRESIDENT TRUMP, CHOOSING TO
PROBE EACH AND EVERY FACET OF
THE PRESIDENT INSTEAD OF GOING
ALL IN ON IMPEACHMENT.
JOINING ME NOW IS ANDY
McCARTHY, FORMER FEDERAL
PROSECUTOR AND FOX NEWS
CONTRIBUTOR.
GOOD TO SEE YOU TONIGHT.
HE WROTE A VERY INTERESTING
PIECE TODAY ABOUT THE
TRUMP TOWER MEETING, BUT FIRST I
WANT TO GET YOUR REACTION TO
WHAT HILLARY CLINTON SAID THERE.
>> I THINK SHE IS AN INTERESTING
PERSON TO HAVE THAT MESSAGE
COMING FROM, SINCE THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT OBVIOUSLY TANKED A
CASE AGAINST HER, BUT■@■@■@@@■@@
KIND OF ATTENTION IS TO@@@@@@@@÷
CALL FOR IMPEACHMENT, IT■÷■÷■÷■R
>> Martha: YEA YOU■@■@NO■÷■÷■÷
WHOLE STORY, AS YOU SAY, THINK
ABOUT THE DESTRUCTION OF SERVERS
WITH HAMMERS AND ALL OF THAT
STUFF, AND YOU HAVE TO WONDER
WHAT KIND OF UNCOMFORTABLE
SUBJECT FOR HER TO TALK ABOUT,
HAVING SUCH AN INVESTIGATION FOR
HERSELF, SHE KNOWS WHAT THAT
FEELS LIKE.
IN "THE WASHINGTON POST" TODAY,
SAYING "WHY IMPEACH?
IN OTHER WORDS, WHEN AN
INVESTIGATION COULD SWING THE
2020 ELECTION, WHY TRY TO
PERSUADE A DOZEN REPUBLICAN
SENATORS TO BOOT TRUMP FROM
OFFICE WHEN YOU COULD TAKE THE
EASIER PATH OF COMMITTING      C
AND VOTERS TO?"
>> I DON'T SEE WHY THOSE THINGS
ARE MUTUALLY EXCLUSIVE.
I'VE NEVER THOUGHT THAT THE
IMPEACHMENT EFFORT WAS ABOUT
IMPEACHING TRUMP, IMPEACHMENT IS
A POLITICAL PROCESS AND PART OF
AN ARRAY OF POLITICAL TOOLS
HERE, I THINK, AND IT HAS ALWAYS
BEEN ABOUT -- OBVIOUSLY IF
SOMETHING FALLS OUT OF THE
INVESTIGATION THOUGH LOOKS LIKE
IT IS FIRE ALARM IMPEACHABLE,
THEY MAY GO FOR IT, BUT I THINK
WHAT THEY ARE TRYING TO DO IS
GRADUALLY DRIVE HIS NUMBERS DOWN
SO HE IS UNELECTABLE BY THE
STRETCH RUN OF THE CAMPAIGN NEXT
YEAR, AND THEREFORE YOU DON'T
REALLY HAVE TO MAKE A CHOICE.
SOME OF THEM CAN PRETEND TO TAKE
THE HIGH ROAD, WHILE JERRY
NADLER AND ADAM SCHIFF AND THE
REST OF THOSE GUYS ON THE
COMMITTEE DO THE SCUT WORK.
>> Martha: THERE IS ALSO A
PIECE TODAY BY ANDREW COHEN,
DONALD TRUMP IS NO
RICHARD NIXON, HE'S WORSE.
IT'S A CONTINUATION OF THAT
NARRATIVE.
DO YOU AGREE WITH THAT
STATEMENT, FIRST OF ALL?
>> I DO THINK WE OUGHT TO PROVE
SOMETHING AGAINST HIM FIRST.
I MEAN, NIXON, IF YOU THINK
ABOUT IT, MARTHA, THE HISTORY OF
THE UNITED STATES, NIXON IS THE
ONLY PRESIDENT WHO REALLY WOULD
HAVE BEEN IMPEACHED IF HE HAD
HUNG ON AND TRIED TO STAY IN
POWER.
WE HAVE NEVER OTHERWISE HAD AN
IMPEACHMENT.
WE HAVE NOW HAD A TWO-YEAR
INVESTIGATION WHERE A FEDERAL
PROSECUTOR FOUND NO CRIMES
AGAINST TRUMP.
I KNOW WE ARE GOING TO HAVE THIS
ARGUMENT ABOUT OBSTRUCTION, BUT
WE ARE ONLY HAVING IT BECAUSE
CONGRESS HAS A DIFFERENT
STANDARD WHEN THEY'RE LOOKING AT
IMPEACHABLE OFFENSES THAN
FEDERAL PROSECUTORS DO.
I THINK THEY OUGHT TO PROVE A
CRIME ON HIM FIRST.
>> Martha: YOU COULD JUST
WRITE "THE STORY" APPARENTLY.
ANDY McCARTHY, GREAT SEEING
YOU TODAY, THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR YOUR GOOD TO SEE YOU
TONIGHT, CIRCUIT >> THANKS,
MARTHA APPEARED TO BE ON REAL
SOON.
YOU BET.
HE IS DEFINITELY RUNNING, THAT
IS THE LINE FROM ED RENDELL, WHO
IS PREPARING A BIG FUND-RAISER
FOR HIS FRIEND, JOE BIDEN.
WHILE THERE'S A LOT OF CONFUSION
AHEAD OF HIS BIG ANNOUNCEMENT,
HE SAYS THAT HIS DEFTLY
HAPPENING.
WE WILL HAVE SOME OF THAT NEXT.
t
safe drivers have to
pay as much for insurance...
As not safe drivers!
AH!
That was a stunt driver.
That's why Esurance has
this DriveSense® app.
The safer you drive,
the more you save.
Don't worry, I'm not
using my phone
and talking to a
camera while driving...
I'm being
towed.
By the way,
I'm actually
a safe driver.
I'm just pretending to
be a not safe driver.
Cool.
Bye Dennis Quaid!
When insurance is affordable,
it's surprisingly painless.
♪
♪♪O■u
♪♪
Applebee's Bigger, Bolder
Grill Combos.
Now that's Eatin Good
in therhood.■■
Your digestive system has
billions of bacteria,
but life cf
balance.
Re-align yourself,
with Align probiotic.
And try Align Gummies,
with prebiotics and probiotics
to help support digestive health
Billions of mouths.
Billions of problems.
Dry mouth? Parched mouth?
Cotton mouth?
There's a TheraBreath for you.
TheraBreath Oral Rinse
and Lozenges.
Help relieve dry mouth
using natural enzymes
to soothe and moisturize.
So you can...
Breathe easy,
there's TheraBreath
at Walmart.
♪ ♪
>> Martha: AFTER MONTHS OF
ANTICIPATION, CONTROVERSY, AND A
LITTLE BIT OF CONFUSION, FORMER
VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN, WE■■■■
UNDERSTAND TODAY, WILL ENT THE
2020 RACE.
HE IS EXPECTED TO ANNOUNCE VIA
VIDEO MESSAGE ON FOR THURSDAY,
THE FIRST OFFçy■;■;■; AT A
çmL IN PITTSBURGH A FEW
DAYS LATER.
JOINING ME NOW, ARI FLEISCHER,
FORMER WHITE HOUSE PRESS
SECRETARY AND FOX NEWS
CONTRIBUTOR BEARD AND ED
RENDELL, FORMER DNC CHAIRMAN AND
PENNSYLVANIA GOVERNOR, WHO IS
HELPING TO ORGANIZE THE
FUND-RAISER FOR THE
FORMER VICE PRESIDENT ON
THURSDAY.
GOOD EVENING TO BOTH OF YOU,
GREAT TO HAVE YOU BOTH HERE.
LET ME START WITH YOU, A LOT OF
EVERYTHING YOU PICK UP AND READ
ON THIS SAYS WE THINK IT IS
GOING TO BE THURSDAY, FIRST IT
WAS GOING FOR A WEDNESDAY IN
CHARLOTTESVILLE, THEN IT WAS
GOING TO BE THURSDAY, AND THEN
THERE WAS A LITTLE TENUOUS MESS
ABOUT THAT, AS WELL.
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
>> I CAN'T TELL YOU, I AM NOT
REALLY AN INSIDER IN THE
CAMPAIGN.
I WAS ASKED TO HELP WITH THE
FUND-RAISER, WHICH IS THAT DAVID
COHEN'S HOUSE, AND I SAID I
WOULD.
GREAT RESPONSES ON THE
FUND-RAISER, I THINK AMONG
DEMOCRATS, THERE IS A REAL
DESIRE TO HAVE JOE BIDEN NOT
ONLY BE AANDIDATE, BUT BE THE
NEXT PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES.
>> Martha: IS THERE ANY PART
OF YOU, ED, THAT FEELS LIKE IT
MIGHT NOT HAPPEN ON THURSDAY?
I KNOW YOU SAY YOU ARE NOT AN
INSIDER, SPOKE TO THE
VICE PRESIDENT TEN DAYS AGO
ABOUT HELPING OUT WITH THIS.
HOW SOLID DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
THURSDAY, AS IN ANNOUNCING DAY?
>> AS IN ANNOUNCING DAY?
WELL, I SUSPECT SOMETHING WILL
HAPPEN ON THURSDAY BECAUSE WE
WOULDN'T BE HAVING THE
FUND-RAISER EVENT UNTIL HE WAS
FORMALLY ANNOUNCED, SO THE
FUND-RAISING EVENT IS IN THE
EVENING, THE EARLY EVENING.
I'M SURE THERE WILL BE SOMETHING
ON THURSDAY.
>> Martha: WHAT DID YOU THINK
ABOUT THE FACT THERE WAS
SCUSSION ABOUT A
CHARLOTTESVILLE ANNOUNCEMENT
ON WEDNESDAY, WHAT DO YOU
MAKE OF THIS ROLLOUT SO FAR?
>> NOTx7■7 CRISP.
MARTHA, IF THERE IS ONE DAY A
CANDIDATE CAN CONTROL, THAT IS
THE ANNOUNCEMENT DAY.
THAT IS 100% A PLAN TODAY, UNDER
THE CAMPAIGNS CONTROL, THE
STAFF'S CONTROL, IT JUST DOESN',
THURSDAY, NO CHARLOTTESVILLE, DO
SOMETHING ELSE, AND THE FOCUS ON
THE FUND-RAISER IS THE OTHER
THING THAT IS JUST A LITTLE BIT
ODD.
YOU WANT YOUR FOLKS TO BE MORE
GRASSROOTS, NOT MONEY.
>> Martha: ED, WHAT YOU SAY TO
THAT?
AND WHAT DO YOU SAY TO THE
UNION, ROLLOUT, SOME PEOPLE LOOK
AT THAT AND IT FEELS A LITTLE
BIT MORE LIKE SOMETHING YOU
MIGHT HAVE DONE A DECADE AGO,
BUT NOT NECESSARILY THE WAY
THINGS WORKED, THE WAY THINGS
HAPPEN TODAY.
>> FIRST OF ALL, I DON'T THINK
ANYONE WHO VOTES STARTING
FEBRUARY OF NEXT YEAR WILL
REMEMBER WHAT THE ROLLOUT WAS.
>> Martha: PROBABLY TRUE.
>> SECONDLY, FOR DEMOCRATS, WE
HAVE TO WIN BACK, THE DEMOCRATS
WHO VOTED FOR DONALD TRUMP IN
2016, THOSE WORKING-CLASS
DEMOCRATS, MOSTLY THE MIDDLE
PART OF THE STATE, FROM AROUND
PITTSBURGH, ET CETERA, A UNION
HALL WITH UNION WORKERS IS A
GOOD MESSAGE TO SEND.
IT'S A MESSAGE TO SAY "HEY,
DONALD TRUMP DIDN'T DO WHAT HE
SAID HE WOULD DO FOR YOU, I'M
THE REAL DEAL."
>> Martha: WE'VE GOT TO LEAVE
IT THERE.
WE'LL HAVE A LOT OF TIME TO TALK
ABOUT THESE, AS YOU SAY, IN THE
ARI AND ED, GREAT TO SEE YOU.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
STILL AHEAD TONIGHT,
BREAKING NEWS ON THE 2020
CANDIDATE THAT HE SAYS CHECKS
ALL THE BOXES FOR THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY, AND IT IS NOT
JOE BIDEN, ACTUALLY.
PLUS, A STORY WITH A 93-YEAR-OLD
WORLD WAR II HERO WHO LOOKS
ABOUT 72, I WOULD SAY.
HE SERVED ON D-DAY, AND ALSO TH
OF THE BULGE.
DO NOT MISS MEETING HIM, COMING
UP.
.
ONE OF THE WINDIEST
PLACES IN AMERICA.
AND HOME TO THREE
BP WIND FARMS.
IN THE OFF-CHANCE TH
STOPS BLOWING HERE...
THE LIGHTS CAN KEEP ON SHINING.
THANKS TO OUR NATURAL GAS.
A SMART PARTNER TO
RENEWABLE ENERGY.
IT'S ALWAYS READY WHEN NEEDED.
OR... NOT.
AT BP, WE SEE
POSSIBILITIES EVERYWHERE.
TO HELP THE WORLD
KEEP ADVANCING.
So in this commercial we see
two travelers
at a Comfort INN with a glow
around them,
so people watching will be like,
"Wow, maybe I'll glow too
if I book direct at
ChoiceHotels.com."
Who glows?
Just say, Badda Book.
Badda Boom.
Book now at ChoiceHotels.com.■
Termites.
We're on the move.
Hey Rick, all good?
Oh yeah, we're good.
We're good.
Terminix.
Defenders of Home.
We humans are
strange creatures.
Other species avoid pain
And struggle.
We actually... seek it out.
Other species do
difficult things
Because they have to.
We do difficult things.
Because we like to.
We think it's... fun.
Introducing the all-new
2019 Ford Ranger
Built for the strangest
of all creatures.
♪ ♪
>> Martha: THE WHITE HOUSE
TODAY CONFIRMING THAT THE
PRESIDENT WILL TRAVEL TO THE
UNITOM AND ALSO FRANCE
IN JUNE TO MARK THE 75TH
ANNIVERSARY OF THE D-DAY LANDIN
LANDING.
"THE STORY" WILL BE THERE, AS
WELL, AND SO WILL MY NEXT GUEST.
GEORGE CHAMPA IS A WORLD WAR II
ARMY VETERAN.
HE WAS AMONG THE 73,000 AMERICAN
SOLDIERS LANDED ON THE SHORES OF
NORMANDY ON JUNE 6TH, 1944.
>> I WAS A SKINNY KID WHEN I
LANDED, A SKINNY,
D-DAY.R-OLD WHEN I LANDED ON
IT WAS FRIGHTENING FOR ME,
AND I HAD A HORRIBLE JOB.
MYLP GATHER THE
ñ■ ANDñ■ WEñ■ñ■ñ■ñ■ñ■ INITIATEDY
CEMETERIES AT NORMANDY AND
THROUGHOUT FRANCE, BELGIUM, AND
GERMANY.
WE INITIATED ABOUT 17 TEMPORARY
CEMETERIES.
HANDLED ABOUT 75,000 DEAD
SOLDIERS, THAT IS AMERICAN AND
GERMAN.
THE GERMANS DIDN'T PICK UP THEI■
I DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME TO TALK,
I UNDERSTAND, SO I WILL JUST
TELL YOU IT WAS A VERY
FRIGHTENING EXPERIENCE BECAUSE I
WAS A NERVOUS LITTLE KID GROWING
UP, TRYING TO GET INTO THE AIR
CORPS, MY EYES WEREN'T QUITE
ENOUGH, S PUT IN AS
A REPLACEMENT FOR THE COMPANY
THAT WAS SHORT ONE NIGHT.
I ENDED UP OVER THERE INñ■ñ■LANE
LOST 18 OF OUR GUYS ON AN
EXERCISE JUST BEFORE THE
INVASION.
WE HAD SIX SURVIVORS, LOST 18 OF
THE FIRST PLATOON, AND SO WE
KNEW THERE WAS A WAR ON WHEN WE
HEARD THAT, NO DRY RUNS.
WE HAD A FEW MOMENTS,
FRIGHTENING MOMENTS ON THE WAY
OVER TO NORMANDY, ALMOST GOT
TORPEDOED, AND A NAVY GUNNER
SHOT THEM DOWN BEFORE WE COULD
RELEASE THE TORPEDO.
THE SHIP ROCKED AND ROLLED,ñ■■■■
UP ON DECK TO FIND OUT WHAT
HAPPENED.
ANYWAY, I WAS IN FIVE CAMPAIGNS
THROUGHOUT FRANCE, BELGIUM, AND
GERMANY, INCLUDING THE BATTLE OF
THE BULGE, AND THEN WE ENDED UP
ABOUT 100 MILES FROM BERLIN,
WHERE WE HAD A TEMPORARY
CEMETERIES THERE THAT WAS
OUR GOVERNMENT DIDN'T WANT ANYg■
OUR GOVERNMENT DIDN'T WANT A■í■E
BODIES HAD TO BE DISINTERR
PRISONERS DIGGING THE GRAVES,
RE-IDENTIFY REMAINS, PUTTING IN@
AND BELGIUM.
>> M■@■@■@■@ KIND OF
WORK YOU DID IS THE KIND OF WORK
A LOT OF
YOU SAW SO MUCH IN ALL OF
CAMPAIGNS.
YOU SAY THAT ABOUT TEN YEARS
AGO, WHEN YOU ARE 81, YOU BECAME
A FILMMAKER AT THAT STAGE OF
THEIR LIVES.
IF YOU COULD JUST GIVE ME -- 30
SECONDS, HALF A MINUTE OR SO,
WHY YOU DECIDED TO DO THAT.
I WILL TRY TO TALK TO YOU IN
NORMANDY AGAIN SO WE CAN
CONTINUE.
GO ON, SIR.■8
TO THIS, BUT IN 2006, IL=L=L=L=D
NONPROFIT, ONLY GOING TO■4■4■4■4
FILM, AND ON■4SITE, YOU CAN
h7h7O
TEAC YOUNG PEOPLE ABOUT THEhmhm.
PEOPLE LIKE ME, THAT DID THE
WORK WE DID COME OF THE MEDICS
DON'T GET MUCH CREDIT FOR WHAT
THEY DID, WE SAW WITH THE HIGH
PRICE OFEDOM IS.
EVERY DAY, FOR 11 MONTHS, THE
COMPANY COLLECTED THE DEAD.
I SAW BODIES IN ALL SHAPES AND
FORMS, AND IT REALLY BOTHERED
ME.
I NEVER FORGOT IT, SO I TELL
PEOPLE, WHEN THEY HEAR THOSE
WORDS "THE HIGH PRICE OF
FREEDOM," YOU HAVE TO REALLY
THINK ABOUT WHAT THAT MEANS THE
RIGHT THAT MEANS SEEING AMERICAN
SOLDIERS, 18, 19, 20, LIKE I
WAS, 18, THAT ARE DEAD.
IN ALL SHAPES AND FORMS.
AND YOU NEVER FORGET THAT.
YOU SEE SOME REALLY TERRIBLE
SITUATIONS.
>> Martha: IT'S AMAZING, AND I
ENCOURAGE EVERY WANT TO GO TO
HER WEBSITE, WHICH IS
LetFreedomRingForAll.org.
AND ALSO YOUNG HISTORY TEACHERS,
SO THEY CAN LEARN ABOUT THE
SACRIFICE THAT WAS MADE.
WE WISH YOU THE BEST OF LUCK,
AND I HOPE WE ARE GOING TO SEE
YOU IN NORMANDY, SIR.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR YOUR
SERVICE AND BEING ON TO BE 26  6
TONIGHT.
>> THANK YOU, MARTHA.
>> Martha: MY THA■■U■■■
.
DEMOCRATIC NOMINATION, BUT
BRIT HUME SAYS THERE IS ONE WHO
STANDS OUT FROM HIS PACK.
HE'S NEXT.
Before discovering Nexium 24HR
to treat his frequent heartburn,
Steven could only imagine
enjoying a spicy taco.
Now, his world
explodes with flavor.
Nexium 24HR stops
acid before it starts
for all-day all-night
protection.
Can you imagine 24-hours
without heartburn?
It's Cedar Plank Seafood time
at Red Lobster!
Featuring three new dishes that
are planked-to-perfection.
Feast on NEW-Plank
Lobster & Shrimp.
Or NEW Colossal Shrimp & Salmon
with a citrusy drizzle.
Tender, smoky, and together
on one plank...
...but not for long-
so hurry in!
Hey Mercedes,
how about letting
your hair down a little?
How about a car for
people who don't play golf?
Hey Mercedes!
Mix it up a little.
How about something for a guy
who doesn't want
a corner office?
Hey Mercedes, I
don't even own a tie.
Do you think I need
a mahogany dashboard?
Hey Mercedes, can you make
it a little cooler in here?
[ A-Class ]
I am setting the temperature
to 68 degrees.
We hear you.
We made a car that does, too.
The all-new A-Class.
All-new thinking
starting at $32,500.
At the Mercedes-Benz
Spring Event.
Going on now.
I don't keep track of regrets.
And I don't add up the years.
But what I do count on...
is BOOST®.
Delicious BOOST®
High Protein Nutritional Drink
has 20 grams of protein,
with 26 essential
vitamins and minerals.
BOOST® High Protein.
Look for savings on BOOST®
in your Sunday paper.
HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN'T GET
HIGH SPEED INTERNET WHERE YOU
LIVE? WELL YOU CAN, WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITE INTERNET WHEREVER YOU
LIVE. HUGHESNET GEN 5 IS FAST.
YOU'LL GET 25MBPS, PLUS BUILT-IN
WI-FI, AND THERE'S NO HARD DATA
LIMITS. SO, WHEREVER YOU LIVE,
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
EVERYTHING YOU LOVE ONLINE.
CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, STAY
INFORMED, WATCH THE LATEST
VIDEOS, AND HELP YOUR KIDS GET■
■■O WONDER HUG■
AMERICA'S NUMBER ONE CHOICE FOR
SATELLITE INTERNET. ACT NOW TO
SAVE BIG WITH OUR LIMITED TIME
OFFER. GET FREE STANDARD
INSTALLATION BY CALLING RIGHT
NOW. SO, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING
FOR? GET HUGHESNET GEN5. TO
ORDER, CALL THE NUMBER ON YOUR
SCREEN. BE SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR
HOME PHONE SERVICE, TOO. CALL
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN
TODAY.
♪ ♪
HOPEFULS JOCKEYING TO POS■
THE DEMOCRATIC SIDE, BUT ONE
NAME IS SEARCHING A BIT RIGHT
NOW AHEAD OF THE PACK, AND THE
NEW POLLS SHOW PETE BUTTIGIEG,
MAYOR OF SOUTH BEND, INDIANA,
KIND OF MOVING UP INTO A SOLID
THIRD PLACE RIGHT NOW, THE FIRST
PRIMARY STATES.
THESE ARE THE POLES THAT ARE THE
MOST INTERESTING, I THINK, WE
LOOK AT NEW HAMPSHIRE OR OHIO --
IOWA.
HE IS IN THIRD PLACE AT 15%
RIGHT NOW, TRAILING ONLY BEHIND
THE POLITICAL HEAVYWEIGHTS OF
BERNIE SANDERS, AND JUST BARELY,
JOE BIDEN, WHO IS SUPPOSEDLY
GOING TO ANNOUNCE LATER THIS
WEEK.
BUTTIGIEG GARNERED ATTENTION ON
THE NATIONAL STAGE AS WELL,
ESTABLISHING HIMSELF AS A SMOOTH
POLITICAL OPERATOR AND WANT TO
WATCH.
WATCH THIS.
>> I THINK HE HAS MADE IT PRETTY
CLEAR THAT HE DESERVES
IMPEACHMENT.
I'M GOING TO LEAVE IT TO THE
HOUSE AND SENATE TO FIGURE THAT
OUT, BECAUSE MY ROLE IN THE
PROCESS IS TO RELEGATE
TRUMP-ISMS TO THE DUSTBIN OF
HISTORY.
PEOPLE SUSCEPTIBLE TO XENOPHOBIA
AND RACISM, WHEN THEY FEEL OUT
OF TOUCH WITH POLITICAL
ENVIRONMENTS THAT THEY ARE IN,
OVERALL, AND WE BETTER PAY
ATTENTION TO THAT.
I WOULD NOT BE RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT TODAY IF I HADN'T COME
OUT.
ONE OF THE THINGS ABOUT
SCRIPTURE IS DIFFERENT PEOPLE
SEE DIFFERENT THINGS IN IT, BUT
THE VERY LEAST, WE SHOULD BE
ABLE T■■ABLISH THAT GOD DOES
NOT HAVE A POLITICAL PARTY.
>> Martha: HERE NOW,
BRIT HUME, FOX NEWS SENIOR
POLITICAL ANALYST.
BRIT, GOOD TO SEE YOU TONIGHT.
DO YOU THINK THIS YOUNG MAN,
THIS MAYOR OF SOUTH BEND, HAS
STAYING POWER?
>> I DO.
I DON'T KNOW THAT HE WILL HAVE
■L■L■L■L37-YEAR-OLD ■@■@■@■@ ISY
BIG TALENT,D@D@D@D@NK YOUD@■@■@T
A TASTE OF THAT IN THE CLIPS
THAT YOU JUST■@ SHOS
IMPEACHMENT, BUT HE IS NOT GOING
TO URGE THAT ON THE ■@@@@@@@■@@K
AB■C■C■C■C■C■C■C■C■C■C■C■CPLE■CC
FEEL ALIONE FOR
TRUMP.■@■@■@■@EATEDLY SAID, MART
HE THINKS IT IS MORE■y■y■ypypypy
ATTACKING TRUMP FOR PEOPLE
TO TRY TO OUT WHYzuzuO MANY
PEOP■p HIM. T■O■O■O■O■O■O■O■OrOF
LITICAL ANALYSIS AND THE RIGHT
WAY TO LOOK AT THIS, FROM THE
POINT OF VIEW OF DEMOCRATS.
YOU KNOW, HIS OFF-THE-CUFF
RESPONSES SEEM TO ME TO BE --
HE'S A VERY, VERY GOOD ON HIS
FEET.
HE WAS IN A RALLY IN IOWA THE
OTHER DAY, I'M SURE YOU SAW THE
CLIP, W SOMEBODY YELLED
ñ■ND GOMORRAH" AT HIM, HE
IS■8■8 GAY.
>> Martha: LET'S TAKE A QUICK
>> THANK YOU.■>■>■>
THE CONDITION OF MY SOUL IS IN■.
>> Martha: YEAH,T IS THE
MOMENT YOU WERE REFERRING TO.
GO AÑkÑk
>> LOOK, HE MIGHT HAVE HAD THAT
IN HIS HIP POCKET, ANTICIPATING
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
T IT DIDN'T SOUND THAT WAY,
DID IT?
HE'S POISED.
THAT WAS A GOOD ANSWER,
POLITICALLY SPEAKING, THAT WAS
PURE GOLD, THAT ANSWER.
LOOK, PERSONALLY, I HAVE ALL
KINDS OF DISAGREEMENTS WITH H,@G
TO ASSESS HIM■p■p■@■@■pL@
TALENT.,@■@■@■@EMS INTELLIGENT .
■@■@■@MS KNOWLEDGEABLE.
HE SEEMS■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■@■pL.,@■E
AND YOUR BERNIE SANDERS OUT
THERE,p@■@p@■@■@■@■@■@p@p@p@p@p@
BUT HE SEE TO MAKE NO EFFORTypyR
LIKABLE.
BUTTIGIEGúy■yúy SEEMS TO BE LIK.
>> Martha: 4 FEET AWAY FROM
HIM THE OTHER NIGHT, I KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT YOU ARE GETTING AT.
>> YOU GOT THE FULL BRUNT.
>> Martha: OH, YEAH.
THERE WAS AN INTERESTING MOMENT,
ONE OTHER BUTTIGIEG MOMENT, WHEN
HE RESPONDED TO THE BACK AND
FORTH HE HAS HAD WITH
MIKE PENCE, AND I DID AN
INTERVIEW WITH RIC GRENELL, WHO
KIND OF WENT AFTER HIM, SAYING
HE WAS LAUNCHING A HATE HOAX
AGAINST MIKE PENCE, AND HERE IS
HOW HE DEALT WITH THAT IN THIS
TOWN HALL APPEARED WATCH THIS.
>> THE CURRENT AMBASSADOR TO
GERMANY, RICHARD GRENELL, IS
ALSO -- HE WEIGHED IN ON THIS,
SAYING YOU'VE BEEN "PUSHING THIS
HATE HOAX ALONG THE LINES OF
JUSSIE SMOLLETT FOR A VERY LONG
TIME NOW, SEVERAL WEEKS."
HOW DO YOU RESPOND TO THAT?
>> ARE NOT A MASTER FISHERMAN,
WHAT I KNOW OBEYED WHEN I SEE
IT, AND I'M NOT GOING TO TAKE
IT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Martha: DO YOU THINK YOU
WILL HAVE TO ANSWER THAT MORE
FULLY?
>> WELL, IT WILL COME UP AGAIN,
I'M SURE.
WHEN PETE BUTTIGIEG WENT AFTER
MIKE PENCE, THEY WERE BOTH IN
INDIANA WHEN PENCILING KNOW
MIKE PENCE WAS GOVERNOR.
HAD A GOOD RELATIONSHIP, AND
PENCE PRAISED BUDDHA        BUT.
WAS TRYING TO GET VICTIM STATUS,
WHICH DOESN'T HURT AS A DEMOCRAT
FOR THE QUESTION WAS INEVITABLE,
AND I DON'T THINK HAD A GOOD
ANSWER.
THE SUBSTANCE OF THE QUESTION,
BUT I THINK THE ANSWER HE GAVE
WAS PRETTY DARN CLEVER.
>> Martha: YEAH.
CHRIS WALLACE HAS A TOWN HALL
COMING UP WITH PETE BUTTIGIEG ON
SUNDAY, MAY 19TH, SO WE WILL BE
WATCHING THAT, BRIT.
>> OKAY, MARTHA, I WILL, TOO.
>> Martha: THANK YOU SO MUCH,
GOOD TO SEE YOU, BRIT HUME AND
WASHINGTON.
MORE OF "THE STORY" NEXT.
Look LiMu. A civilian
buying a new car.
Let's go.
LiMu's right.
Liberty Mutual can
save you money
by customizing your
car insurance,
so you only pay for
what you need.
Oh... yeah, I've been a
customer for years.
Huh...
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
My reputation was
trashed online,
I felt completely helpless.
My entire career and business
were in jeopardy.
I called Reputation Defender.
They were able to restore
my good name.
If you're under attack,
I recommend calling
Reputation Defender.
And consider joining their
groundbreaking campaign
to give every American the
right to remove old,
inaccurateh results by
going to righttobeforgotten.org.
If you have search results that
are wrong or unfair,
call Reputation Defender
at 1-877-866-8555.
If your moderate to severe
ulcerative colitis
or Crohn's symptoms...
are holding you back...
and your
current treatment
hasn't worked
well enough...
it may be
time for a change.
Ask your doctor
about ENTYVIO®,
the only biologic
developed and approved
just for UC and Crohn's.
ENTYVIO® works at the
site of inflammation
in the GI tract,
and is clinically proven
to help many patients
achieve both symptom
relief and remission.
Infusion and s■' reactions
can happen■ ■ ■ fter tr.
ENTYVIO® may
increase risk of infection,
PML, a rare, serious,
potentially fatal
brain infection
caused by a virus
may be possible.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection,
experience frequent
infections
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
If your UC or
Crohn's treatment
isn't working for you,
ask your gastroenterologist
about ENTYVIO®.
ENTYVIO®.
Relief and Remission
within reach.
Six months, six pushups ready.
Up.
Down.
Ah ah!
That's one.
Up.
That's two.
Down.
Get down,
get down.
■7
(ding)
Hey, who are you?
Oh, hey Jeff, I'm a car thief...
What?!
I'm here to
steal your car because,
well, that's my job.
What?
What??
WHAT?!
(laughing)
What??
WHAT?!
What?!
[crash]
WHAT?!
Haha, it happens.
And if you've got
cut-rate car insurance,
paying for this could
feel like getting robbed twice.
So get Allstate...
and be better protected
frolike me.
♪
We're Carvana,
the company who invented
car vending machines and buying
a car 100% online.
Now we've created a brand new
way for you to sell your car.
Whether it's a year old
or a few years old,
we want to buy your car.
So go to Carvana
and enter your license plate,
answer a few questions,
and our techno-wizardry
calculates your car's value
and gives you a real offer
in seconds.
When you're ready,
we'll come to you,
pay you ■ñ
and pick up your c
That's it.
So ditch the old way
of selling your car,
and say hello to the new way--
at Carvana.
>> Martha: THAT IS "THE STORY"
ON THIS TUESDAY NIGHT.
EMAIL US, LET US KNOW WHAT YOU
THOUGHT ABOUT TONIGHT'S SHOW,
INTERVIEW ON RUSH LIMBAUGH, LOVE
TO GET YOUR FEEDBACK THERE.
"THE STORY" CONTINUES FROM
NEW YORK TOMORROW NIGHT AT
7:00 P.M., SO TUNE INTO THAT.
TUCKER CARLSON IS COMING UP
NEXT.
♪ ♪