x■x■■■q■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■q■
So in this commercial
we see two travelers
at a Comfort INN
with a glow around them,
so people watching
will be like,
“Wow, maybe I'll glow too
if I book direct at
ChoiceHotels.com”.
Who glows?
Just say, Badda Book.
Badda Boom.
Ok everyone!
Our mission is to
provide complete,
balanced nutrition
for strength and energy!
Whoo-hoo!
Great-tasting Ensure.
With nine grams of protein
and twenty-six vitamins
and minerals.
Ensure, for strength
and energy.
>> Bill: POWERFUL EARTHQUAKE IN
THE PHILIPPINES CALLING
SIGNIFICANT DAMAGE.
A LAP POOL AND CHILDREN'S POOL
RUPTURED ON TO HAVE OF A
SKYSCRAPER IN MANILA.
WATER CAST INDICATED 600 FEET
TO THE BUILDING BELOW FROM A ■d÷
6.1 MAGNITUDE QUAKE.
11 PEOPLE KILLED.
24 OTHERS LISTED AS MISSING.
NOT A SIGHT YOU SEE ALL THE
TIME.
>> Sandra: A LOT OF DAMAGE.
WE'LL CONTINUE TO WATCH THAT
FOR YOU.
MEANWHILE THIS STORY.
>> MR. GERAGOS AND THE OTHER
ATTORNEY DID NOT ACT WITH
DIGNITY DURING THE COURSE OF
THE CRIMINAL PROCEEDINGS.
WE HOPE THEY FOLLOW OUR LEAD
AND ACT DIGNIFIED DURING THIS
LAWSUIT.
I WILL TELL YOU THIS, THE
SCORCHED EARTH LAWYERING WILL
NOT PLAY OUT IN THE UNITED
STATES DISTRICT COURT IN
CHICAGO.
>> Sandra: WE WATCHED THAT
TOGETHER MOMENTS AGO IN CHICAGO.
ATTORNEYS FOR THE TWO BROTHERS
ANNOUNCING A DEFAMATION SUIT
AGAINST THE LEGAL TEAM
JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
THE BROTHERS DESERVE TO HAVE
THEIR REPUTATIONS CLEARED.
I'M SURE YOU WERE WATCHING THAT
ALONG WITH ALL OF US.
WHAT DID YOU THINK WHEN YOU SAW
THAT, NOW THE BROTHERS FILING
SUIT AGAINST SMOLLETT'S LEGAL
TEAM?
>> ONE OF THE THINGS THAT IS
TROUBLING IS THIS CASE NEVER
WENT TO COURT.
SO THEY WANT TO HAVE THEIR
NAMES D.
THEY WANT TO SEE JUSTICE SERVED.
THEY WANT TO HAVE THE TRUTH
COME OUT SO THAT THE PEOPLE OF
CHICAGO AND THE PEOPLE OF COOK
COUNTY KNOW WHAT ACTUALLY
OCCURRED.
AND SO I KNOW JUSSIE SMOLLETT'S
ATTORNEYS HAVE DONE EVERYTHING
THEY COULD TO KEEP THIS OUT OF
THE COURTROOM.
WE CERTAINLY HAVE A PROBLEM
IN COOK COUNTY BECAUSE THE
STATE'S ATTORNEY HAS DROPPED
ALL CHARGES.
LEADS TO %OTHER PROBLEMS.
AND WE CERTAINLY ENCO
WANTING TO GET TO /TRUTH AND
TO GET PEOPLE TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT OCCURRED AND THAT /
NLY POLICE DID AN
OUTSTANDING JOB OF
INVESTIGATING THIS CASE AND
BRINGING ITFORW[í/ /
AND I /4/THE COURT
CASE WHERE WE CAN FIND OUT AND
THE PEOPLE OF CHICAGO CAN FICX÷1
OUT WHAT HAPPENED.
>> Sandra: WHAT THE SUIT IS
SPECIFICALLY ALLEGING IS THAT
GERAGOS, REPR
SMOLLETT IN ALL OF THIS AND HIS
IN WIDELY REPORTED STATEMENTS
THAT THE BROTHERS .yLED A
CRIMINAL ATTACK AGAINST
SMOLLETT EVEN THOUGH THEY KNEW
IT WASN'T TRUE.
HEARING YOU TALK ABOUT IT
TODAY, THIS IS NOT QUITE A DOWN
IN THE CITY OF■LCHICAGO.
EVERYTHI■L TRANSPIRED
DURING THAT TIME AND DURING
THAT INATIOING   X/,íXíX■X■í■í/M
>> NO, IT HA
WE'VE GOT /7/7/7OTHER ARE
PE
WE #/A PROBLEM /TH
PROR ■X■XIN THIS COUNTY.
ONE OF ■í-- WE'VE GOT PEOPLE
THAT THINK THAT THE LAWS ARE XJ
NOT GOING /7/,/,■■■TO BE ENFORC.
ONE ■)■[■)■■[■)■■)■)■)■■/■)■■■
■)■)■)■)■)■[
THOUGH HE ATTACKED SEVERAL ■/■)
FOR ■)■)■)■[■[■,■,■,■)SPECIAL R
SO THE SITUATION WITH KIM FO
AND THE ■/STATE'S ATTORNEY IN
THIS COUNTY IS■[■
>> Sandra: I WANT TO ASK YOU
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED LAST DNESDA.
30 TEENAGERS WERE ARRESTED IN
THE CITY OF CHICAGO.
HUNDREDS OF STUDENTS, 200
OFFICERS IT TOOK FILLING THE
STREETS OF THE LOOP
NEIGHBORHOOD WHICH IS THE MAIN
BUSINESS DISTRICT IN CHICAGO.
WHAT WAS HAPPENING THAT NIGHT?
>> WELL,  OF THE PROBLEM IS
THAT AS I ALREADY STATED
PEOPLE FEEL THAT THE LAWS■p■÷
AREN'T GOING ■u■u■u■u■u■u■u■u■u.
■u■u■y■y■y■y
PROSECUTE WHAT SHE S ■TO
MINOR CRIMES.
BUT POLICE OFFICERS ARE TTING
HURT.
EY ARING BATTERED.
WE HAVEN'T HAD A CONTRACT IN
TWO YEARS AND  RAISE.
WHAT WE'RE HOPING FOR ■[THAT
THE NEW MAYOR THAT'S COMING
WITH BACK UP THE POLICE
OFFICERS, GET US A ■ ■%CONTRACT.
WE WANT TO WORK WITH THE CITY.
WE WANT TO WORK TO MAKE SURE
CITIES.IS IS ONE OF THE SAFE
>> Sandra: WHAT WAS ■,■,■,
THOUGH?
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT AREAS LIKE
MILLENNIAL PARK, WATER TOWER
PLACE.
SOME OF THE HEAVIEST VISITED
AREAS BY TOURISTS THAT COME
INTO THE CITY OF CHICAGO WHERE
THESE TEENAGERS.
THIS WAS HAPPENING UNTIL SUNDAY
NIGHT.
UPDATE ME WHERE THE TEENS ARE
GATHERING IN THE STREETS AND
TORMENTING INDIVIDUALS AND
STOPPING AND NG ON
WINDOWS OF CARS AS THEY DRIVE
BY.
WHAT MORE CAN YOU TELL US WHAT ?
INCREASED THE NUMBER OF POLICE
OFFICERS.
■■NG FOR THEM TO HIRE
MORE POLICE OF.
WE HASED THE OFFICERS
IN THE DOWNTOWN AREA.■2■2
BUT YOU CAN  CANCEL
SOMEBODY'S DAYS OFF MANY
TIMES.
OUR OFFICERS SOME TIME OFF.
THESE KIDS ARE EMBOLDENED
BECAUSE THERE DOESN'T SEEM TO
BE A CONSEQUENCE FOR THEIR
ACTIONS.
AND WE WANT TO THAT
NARRATIVE.
WE WANT THE NEW TO BACK
UP THE POLICE AND WE WANT TO DO
OUR JOB.
WE WANT TO ■■THIS CITY SAFE
BUT WE CAN'T DO IT BY OURSELVES.
WE x■x■x■x■NEED HELPx■OM THE
POLITICIANS.
x■: WE ALL x■x■x■x■x■THE
POLICE BE ABLE TO DO THEIR
■■■■ñ■ñ■■■■■
WE HEAR YOU.
KEVIN, APPRECIATE YOUR TIME
THIS MORNING.
COME BACK SOON, THANK YOU.
>> Bill: ON THE STEPS OF THE
U.S. SUPREME COURT THE
PLAINTIFFS IN THIS CASE ARGUING
AGAINST OMITTING A CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION ON THE 2020 CENSUS.
THAT WAS THE CASE TODAY BEFORE
THE NINE JUSTICES.
ORAL ARGUMENTS APPEAR TO HAVE
WRAPPED UP.
THE ATTORNEYS ARE REACTING ON
THE STEPS.
WE'LL BRING YOU THE LATEST ON Y;
BACK AFTER THIS.■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
■
- [Woman] With my Shark,
I deep clean messes like this.
This and even this.
But I don't have to clean this,
because the self-cleaning
brush roll removes hair,
while I clean.
- [Announcer] Shark,
the vacuum that deep
cleans, now cleans itself.
300 miles an hour,
that's where I feel normal.
Having an annuity tells me my
retirement is protected.
Learn more at
Retire Your Risk dot org.
>> Bill: MARYLAND GOVERNOR
HOGAN CONSIDERING A RUN FOR
REPUBLICAN TOMORROW NATION AND
TODAY HE IS THE FEATURED
SPEAKER IN KW HAMPSHIRE, A
MUST STOP ON THE TRAIL.
KRISTIN FISHER IS LIVE IN
MANCHESTER LISTENING TODAY.
GOOD MORNING.
>> NO ANNOUNCEMENT FROM
GOVERNOR HOGAN TODAY.
HE CAME TO NEW HAMPSHIRE READY
TO PLAY ACCUSED PRESIDENT TRUMP
OF TRYING TO COMMIT A CRIME,
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE, AND HE
SLAMMED FELLOW REPUBLICANS ALL
OVER THE COUNTRY FOR NOT
JOINING HIM IN SPEAKING OUT.
>> IT'S VERY FRUSTRATING.
AND I KNOW THAT THERE ARE A
NUMBER OF MY COLLEAGUES BOTH
GOVERNORS AND SENATORS AND
MEMBERS OF THE HOUSE WHO WILL
SAY PRIVATELY THEY'RE VERY
CONCERNED BUT THEY WON'T SAY
ANYTHING PUBLICLY BECAUSE
THEY'RE AFRAID.
THERE IS NO PROFILES IN COURAGE
HERE.
>> GOVERNOR HOGAN ANNOUNCED TO
THE REPUBLICAN NATIONAL
COMMITTEE FOR INSISTING ON 100%
LOYALTY TO THE DEAR LEADER.
IN JANUARY THE RNC PASSED A
RESOLUTION OF UNDIVIDED SUPPORT
FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP MERGING THE
PARTY AND HIS REELECTION TEAM
INTO A SINGLE UNIT.
LISTEN TO WHAT THE PARTY
CHAIRWOMAN SAID OF THE
POSSIBILITIES OF REPUBLICANS
JUMPING IN.
>> THEY HAVE TO RIGHT TO JUMP
IN AND LOSE.
THAT'S FINE.
THE PRESIDENT HAS 93% APPROVAL
IN OUR PARTY.
>> BUT GOVERNOR HOGAN INSISTS
THAT IF HE DECIDES TO RUN HE
WOULD NOT BE A SPOILER AND IF
HE DOES RUN, HE BELIEVES THAT
HE MIGHT BE BETTER SUITED THAN
MOST TO ABSORB ANY KIND OF
ATTACKS FROM PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HOGAN SAID TODAY I BATTLED
CANCER FOR 18 MONTHS SO I THINK
>> Sandra: DEMOCRATS DIVIDED ■y
IMPEAC
LAWMAKERS AND 2020 CANDIDATES B■
WE'LL HAVE NEW REACTION ON ALL
OF THAT AT THE TOP OF THE HOUR.
♪
Your digestive system has
billions of bacteria,
but life canhem off
balance.
Re-align yourself■
with Align probiotic.
And try Align Gummies,
with prebiotics and probiotics
to help support digestive health
What makes these simple dishes
the best simple dishes ever?
Great tasting, heart-healthy
California Walnuts.
So simple, so go
Get the recipes at walnuts.org.
THE S&P 500 IS ON PACE FOR A
RECORD CLOSE, THE FIRST OF 2019.
FOR THOSE KEE