>> Greg: ARE THOSE THE TULIPS?
>> Emily: YES.
>> Greg: TAKE YOULD TO
WORK AND EARTH DAY TO BRING SOME
EARTH TO WORK DAY.
EVERYBODY BRING A PAIL OF DIRT
AND POUR IT ON YOUR BOSSES DESK.
DO IT TOMORROW.
SET YOUR DVR, NEVER MISSED AN
EPISODE OF "THE FIVE" ," "SPECIL
REPORT" IS UP NEXT.
HEY, BRET.
>> Bret: HEY, GREG, HAPPY
EARTH DAY.
HOUSE DEMOCRATS ARE TEARING DOWN
ANOTHER GAUNTLET IN A BIGGER
BATTLE OVER THE MUELLER REPORT,
THERE WOULD BE A POINT MAN FOR
IMPEACHMENT, JERRY NADLER HAS
SUBPOENAED A WHITE HOUSE INSIDER
IN A FUTURE PLAYER IN THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL NARRATIVE,
FORMER WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL DON
MCGANN IS THE SUBJECT OF THAT
SUBPOENA.
THE WEIGHTING RESPONSE FROM THE
TRUMP TEAM, JOHN ROBERTS STARTS;
0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0;
0;0;0;0;UN0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0>0;0E
ALSINT HOW MUCESSLEARN AGAT ISY
KNOWN.
INTE0;IM,■>ERT M0;0;
0;L■>0;0;0;UCTION O
JUSTICE.
BUT THIS IS■v■>■v■>■>■v■v■v■v vS
SHORT OF IMPEACHMENT, NO DOUBT
WILL TIE THE WHITE HOUSE IN
KNOTS.■■/
>> AT THE ANNUAL EASTER EGG
ROLL, PRESIDENT TRUMP WEIGHED IN
ON TALK OFMENT, TAKING A
WHAT?■u
ME, WORRY?
APPROACH.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT?
>> THE PRESIDENT'S CONFIDENCE
WOULD SHOW THE SINKING OF THE
DEMOCRATIC LEADERSHIP, AND HOUSE
SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI WRITING
WHILE OUR VIEW RAINS FROM
PERCEIVING THE INVESTIGATION OF
THE MUELLER REPORT TO
IMPEACHMENT, WE ALL FIRMLY AGREE
THAT WE SHOULD PROCEED DOWN A
PATH OF FINDING THE TRUTH.
IT IS ALSO IMPORTANT TO KNOW
THAT THE FACTS REGARDING HOLDING
THE PRESIDENT ACCOUNTABLE CAN BE
GAINED OUTSIDE OF IMPEACHMENT
HEARINGS, THE ONE THAT WOULD
TAKE UP IMPEACHMENT APPEARED TO
HESITATE WHEN ASKED.
>> Bret: DO YOU THINK THAT
THIS IS IMPEACHABLE?
>> YEAH, I DO.
IF PROVEN, IF PROVEN, WHICH HAS
NOT BEEN PROVEN YET, SOME OF
THIS COULD BE IMPEACHABLE, YES.
>> WHILE SOME 2020 DEMOCRATIC
CANDIDATES HAVE STAYED AWAY FROM
ANY TALK OF IMPEACHMENT,
ELIZABETH WARREN SEEKING A BOOST
TO THE LEGGING CAMPAIGN SAYS
THAT SHE IS ALL IN.
>> I JUST CALLED ON THE HOUSE TO
INITIATE IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDINGS.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP MOCKS SUCH
TALK FIRING BACK ONLY HIGH
CRIMES AND MISDEMEANORS CAN LEAD
TO IMPEACHMENT.
THERE WERE NO CRIMES BUT I MEANO
U CANNOT IMPEACH.
IT WAS THE DEMOCRATS THAT
COMMITTED THE CRIMES, NOT YOUR
REPUBLICAN PRESIDENT.
THE PRESIDENT WAS ALSO ON
OFFENSE ON THE FINANCIAL FRONT,
SUING CHAIRMAN ELIJAH CUMMINGS
FOR TRYING TO SUBPOENA FINANCIAL
RECORDS FROM THE ACCOUNTING
FIRM.
IN THE LAWSUIT TRUMP ATTORNEYS
ATTACKING THE SUBPOENA WRITING
"IT'S GOAL IS TO EXPOSE
PLAINTIFF'S PRIVATE
INFORMATIONAL FOR THE SAKE OF
EXPOSURE THAT IT WILL TURN UP
SOMETHING THAT DEMOCRATS CAN USE
■■■ TOOL AGAINST THE
PRESIDENT NOW AND IN THE 2020
ELECTION."
SOURCES SAY THAT THE SUBPO
GOES WELL BEYOND REQUEST FOR THE
PRESIDENT'S FINANCIAL RECORDS,
ALSO SEEKING THOSE AND ALL OF
HIS CHILDREN INCLUDING BARRON
AND TIFFANY TRUMP, MICHAEL
COHEN, A FELON WHO HAS PLEADED
GUILTY TO CONGRESS SAYS THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAD MISREPRESENTED HIS
NET WORTH WHEN HE WAS A PRIVATE
CITIZEN.
ELIJAH CUMMINGS APPEARED
UNFAZED.
IN A STATEMENT THIS AFTERNOON
SAYING THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS A
LONG HISTORY OF TRYING TO USE
BASELESS LAWSUITS TO ATTACK HIS
ADVERSARIES.
BUT THERE WAS SIMPLY NO VALID
LEGAL BASIS T0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0;0;;
THE DULY AUTHORIZED SUBPOENA
FROM CONGRESS.
THE ATTORNEYS INSISTE0; THAT HE
HAS LONG0;0;0;0;0;N UNDER THIS
GUARANTY OF THEAL A
THAT IT IS0;0;0;0;0; THE IRS PUT
CONGRESS IS TO LOOK INTO0;0;0;0S
LOOKED AT PRESIDENT TRUMP FOR
YEARS UPON YEARS AND0;0;0; HAS D
NO REASON TO BRING ANY KIND OF
ACTION CIVIL OR CRIMINAL AGAINST
THE PRESIDENT.
>> Bret: CHAIRMAN NADLER
DROPPED THE SUBPOENA AS HOUSE
DEMOCRATS ARE MEETING ON THIS
CONFERENCE CALL ABOUT NEXT STEPS
AFTER THE MUELLER REPORT.
THE WHITE HOUSE DID NOT HOLD
BACK, DID NOT ISSUE EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE FOR ANY OF THOSE
MUELLER REPORT OR THE TESTIMONY
BEFORE, IS THERE A THOUGHT THAT
THEY MAY STEP UP AGAIN0;0;0;0;0?
>> WE DO NOT  IF0;0;0;0;0;0;0; E
GOING TO EXERT EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE, TESTIFYING BEFORE
CONGRESS, BUT THE ENTIRE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION THAT CONTAINED
UNDER ARTICLE TWO OF THE
INVESTIGATION WHICH IS THE
EXECUTIVE BRANCH.
REALLY IT WAS DON MCGANN, THE
MEMBER OF THE EXECUTIVE BRANCH
TALKING TO ANOTHER MEMBER WHEN
IT CAME TO THE MUELLER
QUESTIONING.
BUT IF CONGRESS WERE TO SUBPOENA
HIM, THEN THAT IS ARTICLE 1 OF
THE CONSTITUTION AGAINST ARTICL.
I ASSUME THAT THE
PRESIDENT UNDER THAT PREMISE
WOULD BE ABLE TO EXERT EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE.
IT WOULD BE SOMEWHAT DIFFERENT.
TO THE POINT IS THAT THEY DID
NOT EXERT EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE
OVER THE RELEASE OF THE MUELLER
REPORT.
BECAUSE THEY DID NOT DO THAT,
MAYBE YOU ARE IN A PROBLEM TO
PUT THE TWO FACE BACK INTO THE
TUBE IN TERMS OF WHETHER THEY
DID NOT EXERT EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE FOR DON MCGANN TALKING
TO MUELLER, THIS IS DIFFERENT
BECAUSE IT IS THE ADMINISTRATION
AND CONGRESS, TWO DIFFERENT
BRANCHES OF GOVERNMENT.
>> Bret: UNCHARTED WATERS
EITHER WAY, SENIOR POLITICAL
ANALYST BRIT HUME IS WITH US
TONIGHT.
WE MENTIONED THAT THE CONFERENCE
CALL HAS BEEN GOING ON.
DEMOCRATS CONSIDERING THE WAY
FORWARD, SOME VERY AGGRESSIVELY
SAYING THAT IT NEEDS TO GO DOWN
IN IMPEACHMENT ROAD.
THE KEY THING IS INTENT, RIGHT?
>> RIGHT, THERE ARE THINGS IN
THE MUELLER REPORT THAT TRUMP
AND HIS ALLIES MAY HAVE DONE
THAT ONE COULD BE PULLED
TOGETHER IN SOME IMPEACHMENT
ARTICLE FOR OBSTRUCTION.
BUT THERE ARE SOMETHINGS THAT
WOULD BE PROBLEMATIC, ONE OF
THEM IS INTENT.
THE ONE THING OF COURSE, WE NOW
KNOW THAT THE THING THAT THE
PRESIDENT WAS BEING INVESTIGATED
FOR POTENTIALLY CRIMINAL HE WAS
CONSPIRACY OR COOPERATION WITH
THE RUSSIAN ATTEMPT TO
INTERFERE, INFLUENCE THE
ELECTION, HE HAS BEEN CLEARED OF
THAT NOW.
SO HE WOULD HAVE BEEN
OBSTRUCTING AN INVESTIGATION
INTO SOMETHING HE DID NOT DO.
THAT WOULD WAY, THAT WOULD VEER
ON THE QUESTION OF INTENT,
CRIMINAL INTENT.
AND REMEMBER WHEN JAMES COMEY
DECLINED TO PROSECUTE
HILLARY CLINTON FOR MISHANDLING
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION, WHAT WAS
MISSING IN THE END?
AND WHAT TURNED THE TIDE?
A LACK OF INTENT, THAT PROVES
HOW IMPORTANT IT WOULD BE.
IN ADDITION, THERE IS THIS, IF
THEY WERE TO PROCEED AGAINST THE
PRESIDENT ON THIS SET OF FACTS,
AND IT IS HARD TO IMAGINE THAT
THE CONGRESSIONAL INVESTIGATION
WILL HONOR ANYTHING THAT ROBERT
MUELLER WITH THE INVESTIGATIVE
RESOURCES DID NOT TURN UP, IF
THEY WERE TO TRY TO DO THAT,
THEY MIGHT KEEP THEIR EYE ON ONE
THING, AND THE FACT THAT THEY
HAVE INVESTIGATIONS GOING ON
WITHIN THE DEPARTMENT OF
JUSTICE, ONE INSPECTOR GENERAL'S
INVESTIGATION, AND YOU HAVE A
PROSECUTOR NAMED HUBER OUT IN
UTAH WHO WAS SUPPOSED TO LOOK
INTO MISCONDUCT IN THE HANDLING
OF THE BEGINNING OF THIS
INVESTIGATION.
AND IF THOSE THINGS WERE TO
BRING -- BEAR FRUIT WITH
INFORMATION THAT CAST DOUBT ON
LEGITIMACY OF THE WHOLE THING,
THAT WOULD ARISE RIGHT IN THE
MIDDLE OF WHAT WOULD BE THE
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDING, AND IT
WOULD PRESENT A SERIOUS
POLITICAL PROBLEM FOR A VOTE TO
IMPEACH.
>> Bret: THIS IS A CONUNDRUM
FOR SOME DEMOCRATS, NANCY PELOSI
HAS SIGNALED PUTTING ON THE
BRAKES WHILE OTHERS ARE GOING
FULL STEAM AHEAD.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, AND I THINK
THAT NOW THAT ELIZABETH WARREN
IS OUT SAYING THAT THE
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDING SHOULD
BEGIN, WITHIN THAT JOSTLING IT
HAS TO GET PRETTY SERIOUS WITH
ALL OF THOSE CANDIDATES RUNNING
ON THE DEMOCRATIC SIDE.
THAT -- SHOULD THAT QUESTION
WILL BE PUT TO EACH AND EVERY
ONE OF THESE CANDIDATES,
IMPEACHMENT OR NOT, AND THEY ARE
GOING TO HAVE TO FACE UP TO IT,
AND SOME OF THEM MAY WANT TO
THINK THAT IT IS A BAD IDEA
POLITICALLY TO BE UNDER THAT
ROAD, BUT THEY WILL BE UNDER
PRESSURE TO DO IT.
AND IT IS IMPORTANT AS A LARGE
BASIS OF THE PARTY THAT WILL
WANT IMPEACHMENT, SIGNIFICANT
MAJORITIES SAY THAT THEY WANT
HIM IMPEACHED, SO WE WILL
PROBABLY HEAR MORE ABOUT THIS,
AND IT DOES PRESENT AN ISSUE FOR
THE LEADERSHIP IN THE CONGRESS
AND ALSO FOR SOMEONE TRYING TO
GET ELECTED PRESIDENT, BECAUSE
IMPEACHMENT HOLDS SOME RISKS.
>> Bret: IT DEFTLY Dñ;■■■ññ■■ññ7
■4O■■■■■■7■■■/■/■/■|■737373|■|■W
APPROACHING 20.■ú■q■/■■■■■■■■■■.
EXz ■ ■ -KNOWN FZPHE■ç■ç■ç■■ç■■■
■8/&/&■>■> FORMER VICE PRESIDEN-
VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN.
THE EVER-EXPANDING DEMOCRATIC
FIELD.
>> 2020 IS 19TH CANDIDATE SETH
MOULTON FROM MASSACHUSETTS.
AND HE IS MUSING ABOUT MUELLER.
>> WHEN THE PRESIDENT TWEETED
THAT THIS IS THE GREATEST
WITCH HUNT IN AMERICAN HISTORY,
I SAID AS THE REPRESENTATIVE OF
SALEM, MASSACHUSETTS, I CAN SAY
THAT THAT IS FALSE.
>> HE ALSO PLANS TO FOCUS HIS
PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN ON
NATIONAL SECURITY, BUT THE
WHITE HOUSE HAS DOUBTS ANOTHER
CANDIDATE FROM MASSACHUSETTS
ELIZABETH WARREN IS EXPLAINING
HOW SHE PAID FOR A
1.25 TRILLION PLAN TO CANCEL UP
TO $50,000 IN STUDENT LOAN DEBT
R 42 MILLION PEOPLE, AND COVER
TUITION AT PUBLIC COLLEGES.
SHE WRITES "THE ENTIRE COST OF
MY BROAD DEBT CANCELLATION PLAN
AND UNIVERSITY FREE COLLEGE IS
COVERED BY MY ULTRA MILLIONAIRE
TAX.
WHILE SHE IS ADDING POLICY
PROPOSALS, BETO O'ROURKE IS
LOSING PERSONNEL, BECKY BOND
ANZAC MALLETS BOTH A1p1p1p■p■p■÷
CAMPAIGN OH ACCORDING TO A
BUZZFEED, AND PETE BUTTIGIEG IS
MAKING HEADLINES FOR THE
ECONOMY.
>> A LOT OF NEIGHBORS AND
FAMILIES ARE LIVING LIKE THE
RECOVERY NEVER HAPPENED.
IT JUST KIND OF TURNS YOU
AGAINST THE SYSTEM IN GENERAL,
AND YOU MORE THAN LIKELY WANT TO
VOLOW THE
WHICH COULD LEAD TO
DERSOMETHING
RO
TWITTER, COME ON, PETE
BUTTIGIEG, IT IS IN AND
ACTUALLY -- INTELLECTUALLY
INTELLIGENT TO COMPARE THE TWO,
AND HE IS WITHIN THE MARGIN OF
ERROR OF JOE BIDEN.
BERNIE SANDERS BY DOUBLE DIGITS,
NOW THEY ARE LOOKING FORWARD TO
AN EXPECTED WEDNESDAY CAMPAIGN
ANNOUNCEMENT.
>> WITH THE RISE OF
SENATOR SANDERS AND DONALD TRUM
DONALD TRUMP'S POPULARITY, THAT
COMBINATION REALLY A COUPLE OF
THINGS, IT TAKES THE WHOLE AGE
FACTOR OUT OF THE EQUATION, AND
IT GOES BACK TO■■xx■■#■#■#■#BERE
POLE FOR DEMOCRATS, WHO IS A
CANDIDATE THAT IS BEST TO BEAT
DONALD TRUMP?
>> MOST OF THE REMARKS THIS YEAR
HAVE BEEN IN CONFERENCES WHERE A
CROWD WAS ALREADY GOING TO BE
THERE FOR SOMETHING ELSE.
IF YOU REALLY PLANS TO HOST A
RALLY OR RALLIES, IT WILL BE A
TESTAMENT OF THE STAR POWER TO
SEE WHO SHOWS.
NOBODY SAID WHEN OR WHERE
JOE BIDEN SUPPORTERS COULD GO.
>> Bret: IT IS INTERESTING TO
SEE MAYOR PETE LEADING ELIZABETH
WARREN IN NEW HAMPSHIRE.
>> MAY BE IT CHANGES WHEN
JOE BIDEN GETS AND IF HE DOES.
>> Bret:■ THANK YOU.■/■/■■■■■/ñA
■>■>TK&TOTAL SUR SAYING THAT OFS
FAILED TO HEED WARNINGS FROM
DIFFERENT INTELLIó ■>■>■>■á■>■á■
INCLUDINEAST FOUR
AMERICANS DEAD.w>■767■7RE■■/■■■■
INTERNATIONAL TERRORIST GROUPS.
BENJAMIN HALL HAS OUR STORY.&a
>> ANOTHER TODAY AFTER
NINE COORDINATE A BLAST KILLED
AT LEAST 290 AND INJURED 500
YESTERDAY.
MONDAY'S EXPLOSION CAME AS
FOUND MORE BOMBS IN■p
AND TRY TO DEFUSE THEM.
THREE PACK CHURCHES WERE CHARTED
ON EASTER SUNDAY LEAVING
BLOOD-SOAKED PEWS AT
ST. ANTHONY'S THAT SAW MUCH OF
THE CARNAGE, THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION HAS OFFERED
ASSISTANCE.
>> I SPOKE WITH THE
PRIME MINISTER.
I SPOKE WITH THE VARIOUS
GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS, AND WE ARE
WORKING WITH SRI LANKA.
SPEAKS OF >> LUXURY HOTELS WERE
ALSO HIT THE TOURIST AS TARGETS]
AND 31 FOREIGNERS DIED, AMONG
THEM SEVERAL AMERICANS INCLUDING
A FIFTH-GRADER FROM D.C. AND A
40-YEAR-OLD FROM DENVER, CARRIED
OUT BY SEVEN SUICIDE BOMBERS
FROM A LITTLE-KNOWN DOMESTIC
GROUP NAMED NATIONAL THOWFEEK
JAMAATH.
POLICE CARRIED OUT RAIDS ACROSS
THE CAPITAL.
A 24 SUSPECTS ARE IN CUSTODY
ALL SRI LANKAN.
BUT TODAY BELIEVE THAT THE GROUP
WAS HELD BY AM
BY A INTAL TER
NETWORK.
NOW ADMITTING THAT THEY RECEIVED
A TIP-OFF TEN DAYS A FROM
INTERNATIONAL AGENCIES THAT
SUICIDE BOMBERS WOULD ATTACK,
BUT APPEARED NOT TO DO ANYTHING.
>> THEY HAVE SAID THAT THE
TARGETS ARE THE CHRISTIAN AND
CATHOLIC CHURCHES, AND ALSO THE
DESTINATIONS.
OKAY.
>> IT IS NOT KNOWN■O■OZO■O WHO E
ATTACKERS, BUT OVER 40 SRI
LANKANS FOUGHT WITH ISIS IN IRAQ
AND SYRIA.
GRIEF AND SHOCK WAS VISIBLE
ACROSS THE CAPITAL IS THE ONLY
NATION TRY TO COME TO TERMS WITH
THE ATROCITIES.
THE COUNTRY IS IN A STA
EMERGENCY AND SRI LANKA'S
PRESIDENT HAS GIVEN THE MILITARY
SWEEPING WARTIME POWERS TO
ARREST AND DETAIN --
>> AS THE NETWORK GETS UNDERWAY,
THE U.S. HAS ISSUED A TRAVEL
ADVISORY WARNING SAYING THAT
THERE ARE THREATS POTENTIALLY OF
MORE ATTACKS.
>> Bret: BENJAMIN HALL LIVE IN
LONDON, THANK YOU.
THIS IS ANOTHER FOX NEWS ALERT,
NORTH KOREAN STATE MEDIA HAS
JUST ANNOUNCED THAT LEADER KIM
JONG UN WILL VISIT RUSSIA AND
MEET WITH VLADIMIR PUTIN, THE
SESSION HAS BEEN IN THE WORKS
FOR A WHILE, TODAY THE COMMUNIST
NATION MADE THAT OFFICIAL.
A DATE FOR THE VISIT HAS NOT
BEEN ANNOUNCED.
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S CAMPAIGN TO
TRY TO DRY UP OIL REVENUES FOR
IRAN AND STEP UP THE PRESSURE ON
ISLAMIC REPUBLIC IS GOING INTO
OVERDRIVE TONIGHT.
THE U.S. SAYS IT WILL NOT EXTEND
WAIVERS TO A HANDFUL OF
COUNTRIES STILL ALLOWED TO BUY
OIL WITHOUT FACING AMERICAN
SANCTIONS.
RICH EDSON TELLS US WHAT THAT
MEANS.
>> IF YOU DON'T ABIDE BY THE
SAME CHAIN --
>> THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
ESCALATES THE CAMPAIGN AGAINST
IRAN TARGETING THE OIL EXPERTS.
>> ANY AGENCY SHOULD DO ITS
DILIGENCE AND ERROR ON THE SIDE
OF CAUTION.
THE RISKS ARE SIMPLY NOT GOING
TO BE WORTH THE BENEFITS.
>> NOVEMBER THE UNITED STATES
GRANTED EIGHT COUNTRIES, SEVERAL
OF THEM U.S. ALLIES WAIVERS TO
ALLOW THEM TO CONTINUE BUYING
IRANIAN OIL, THOSE EXPIRE EARLY
NEXT MONTH, SECRETARY MIKE
POMPEO SAYS■ T THE U.S. WILL
REFUSE TO EXTEND ANY OF THEM,
CHINA IS A TOP IMPORTER OF
IRANIAN OIL.
>> THEY OPPOSE THE INTERNATIONAL
SANCTIONSOSED BY THE U.S.
>> LAST WEEK TURKISH GOVERNMENT
EXPECTED THE U.S. WOULD EXTEND
ITS WAIVER.
"TURKEY REJECTS UNILATERAL OF
SANCTIONS AND HOW TO NEGOTIATE
WITH NEIGHBORS."
-- OTHER SAY THAT THEY HOPE THE
ADMINISTRATION WILL LET THEM
CONTINUE.
POMPEO SAYS THAT THE U.S. WILL
FORCE THE SANCTIONS AS PART OF
THE WITHDRAWAL FROM THE IRANIAN
NUCLEARvT
ANYONE OIL FROM IRAN HAS
BEEN LIVING ON BORROWED TIME.
THE PRICE OF CRUDE OIL SPIKED ON
NEWS OF THE ADMINISTRATION'S
POLICY.
THEY■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
ADMINISTRATION OFFICIAL SAYS
THAT IT IS TYPICAL OF THEIR
BEHAVIOR.
>> Bret: AT THE
STATE DEPARTMENT, THANKS.
UP NEXT, SOON PRESIDENT TRUMP
WILL NOT BE THE ONLY FORMER TV
STARTED TO RUN A COUNTRY.
THE LATEST■■ ADDITION TO Ay VER.
FIRST WHAT SOME OF THE FOX
AFFILIATES AROUND THE COUNTRY
ARE COVERING TONIGHT HERE IN
MIAMI AS FLORIDA LAWMAKERS
CONSIDER SEVERAL MEASURES TO
ADDRESS THE STATE'S LONG
DOCUMENTED ELECTION BLOWS.
NEW REPUBLICAN SPONSOR BILL WILL
STREAMLINE THE BALLOTCHEDULE!8!■
AND■■■xÑ■#■#■■t■■■BALLOTTURE■/■7
TH STOP
SUPERMARKET WORKERS AND
OFFICIAL ST THE■
EACHED A TENTATIVE
CONTRACT AGREEMENT, UNION
MEMBERS HAVE BEEN ON STRIKE
SINCE APRIL 11TH.
THE WALKOUT BEGAN OVER THE
COMPANY'S PROPOSED CUTS TO
HEALTH CARE, TAKE-HO AND
OTHER BENEFITS.
AND THIS IS A■■ LIVE LOOK AT
SAN FRANCISCO FROM THE AFFILIATE
FOX 2, ONE OF THE BIG STORIES
TONIGHT, TESLA CEO ELON MUSK
READY TO TRANSFORM CARS INTO
DRIVERLESS VEHICLES.
AT THE HEADQUARTERS, SOME
EXPERTS ARE SKEPTICAL WHETHER
THE TECHNOLOGY HAS ADVANCED TO
WHERE THE CARS CAN BE DRIVEN
SOLELY BY ROBOTS WITHOUT A HUMAN
TO TAKE CONTROL IF SOMETHING
GOES AWRY.
THAT IS TWO NIGHTS LIVE LOOK
OUTSIDE THE BELTWAY IN "SPECIAL
REPORT," WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪ ♪
LiMu's right.
Liberty Mutual can
save you money
by customizing your
car insurance,
so you only pay for
what you need.
Oh... yeah, I've been a
customer for years.
Huh...
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
♪♪
Can we talk?
We used to play so
beautifully together.
Now we can barely
play anything...
Even cards with the girls.
If you have bent fingers,
and can't lay your hand flat,
talk to your doctor.
It may be
Dupuytren's contracture.
Your hand is talking.
Isn't it time you listened?
There are nonsurgical options.
Take the first step.
And learn more about
Dupuytren's.
At FactsOnHand.com
♪♪
My mom washes the dishes...
...before she puts them in the
dishwasher.
So what does the dishwasher do?
Cascade Platinum does the work
for you,
prewashing and removing
stuck-on foods,
the first time.
Wow, that's clean!
Cascade Platinum.
♪ ♪
>> Bret: ON THIS EARTH TODAY,
NEW YORK CITY'S MAYOR SAYS THAT
HIS CITY HAS ITS OWN GREEN NEW
DEAL.
OR A NEW GREEN DEAL, DEMOCRAT OF
BILL de BLASIO TELLS MSNBC
THAT HE WANTS TO BAN GLASS AND
STEEL SKYSCRAPERS.
HE SAYS THEY ARE INCREDIBLY
ENERGY INEFFICIENT.
HE IS ALSO TALKING ABOUT
MILLIONS OF DOLLARS IN FUNDS FOR
COMPANIES THAT DO NOT RETROFIT
THEIR BUILDINGS.
ALSO SAYING THAT HE WILL MAKE  A
DECISION SOON ABOUT WHETHER HE
WILL JOIN THE DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL PRIMARY FIELD.
ANOTHER GRIM WARNING ABOUT
MEDICARE AND SOCIAL SECURITY,
THE GOVERNMENT REPORT SAYS THAT
BOTH ARE ON INCREASINGLY SHAKY
GROUND.
MEDICARE IS POINTED TOWARDS
INSOLVENCY BY 2026,
SOCIAL SECURITY WOULD FOLLOW
NINE YEARS LATER.
THE REPORT URGES LAWMAKERS TO
TAKE ACTION SOONER RATHER THAN
LATER, SOMETHING THAT CONGRESS
HAS BEEN UNWILLING TO DO IN THE
PAST.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS THAT HERMAN
CAIN HAS WITHDRAWN FROM
CONSIDERATION FOR A SEAT ON THE
FEDERAL RESERVE'S BOARD OF
GOVERNOR CEO AT THE PIZZA PARLOR
WHO DROPPED OUT OF THE 2012
PRESIDENTIAL RACE AMID
ALLEGATIONS OF SEXUAL HARASSMENT
AND INFIDELITY, THE ISSUES
RESURFACEDFTER THE PRESIDENT
SAID THAT HE INTENDED TO
NOMINATE KANE TO THE CENTRAL
BANK'S BOARD.
McSTAY ON WALL STREET, THE DOW
POINTS, THE S&P 500
WAS UP THREE, THE NASDAQ
FINISHED AHEAD 17.
LIFE IS IMITATING ART, OR AT
LEAST TELEVISION IN UKRAINE
TONIGHT, THE COMEDIAN WHO PLAYS
A TEACHER WHO ENDS UP BEING
PRESIDENT, HE IS REALLY ABOUT TO
BECOME PRESIDENT.
SENIOR FOREIGN AFFAIRS
CORRESPONDENT AMY KELLOGG
NT OF THE PEOPLE.
>> IT WAS A SLAM-DUNK FOR THE
SERVANT OF THE PEOPLE, THAT IS
THE NAME OF THE SITCOM THAT
BECAME ITS NAME OF THE POLITICAL
PARTY, AND NOW IT IS HIS MANDAT
MANDATE.
THE COMEDIAN PLAYS A HISTORY
TEACHER WHO AFTER A RANT ABOUT
CORRUPTION GOES VIRAL GETS
ANOINTED AS PRESIDENT OF THE
UKRAINE.■8
THEIR■p■p IS THE SECOND
POOREST IN EUROPE AND FIVE YEARS
INTO A WAR, COULD TURN OVER A
NEW LEAF JUST LIKE IN THE TV
SHOW.
THE UNITED STATES
EUROPEAN UNION, GERMANY, AND
FRANCE CONGRATULATED THE NEW
PRESIDENT.
THE POLITICIANS IN MOSCOW MORE
TEPID, LOOKING FOR STEPS BY THE
NEW LEADER BEFORE MAKING
JUDGMENT.
INCLUDING A JOKE IN HIS VICTORY
REMARKS.
>> HAD MY WIFE HEARD ALL THE
THINGS SAID ABOUT ME DURING THE
CAMPAIGN, SHE WOULD NEV
ME.
>> BRINGING UKRAINIAN PRISONERS
OF WAR BACK HOME INCLUDING THE
24 SAILONATCHED RUSSIA IN
THE CURSE STRAIGHT TO LAST YEAR.
THE INCUMBENT WAS CRITICIZED FOR
NOT IMPROVING THE LIVES OF
UKRAINIANS AND NOT ENDING THE
CONFLICT IN THE.t
>> I SUPPORT HIM■■■■■■IMPROVE AG
BETTER.
BECAUSE WE ARE TIRED OF SUCH
LIFE.
>> OTHERS THINK THAT THINGS CAN
IN FACT GET MUCH WORSE IN THE
UKRAINE.
>> I'M A BEAR SUCH A PERSON CAN
LEAD THE COUNTRY AFTER ALL THAT
IS HAPPENING HERE.
SPEAK OF THE FRESH-FACED IN
EASTERN POLITICS SAYS THAT HIS
THAT AN ALL THE SOVIET STATES,
ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE.
THAT MAY HAVE BEEN A MESSAGE FOR
THE RUSSIANS.
HIS CALL WITH PRESIDENT TRUMP
UNDERSCORING THE U.S.'S
UNWAVERING SUPPORT FOR UKRAINE
SOLVENT WILL ENACT SOVEREIGNTY.
>> Bret: A REPORT OUT OF
PAKISTAN SAYS THAT THEY HAVE
ARRESTED REMAINING TERRORIST IN
THE 2002 JOURNALIST.
THE AL QAEDA OFFSHOOT IS SAID TO
BE A TRAINER OF SUICIDE BOMBERS,
AN AMERICAN MILITIA LEADER IS
ACCUSED OF ILLEGALLY OBTAINING
IMMIGRANTS AT THE SOUTHERN
BORDER.
WE WILL BRING YOU THERE.
♪ ♪ri
With a Terrain Management
System for... this.
An Electronic Locking Rear
A Differential for...hat.■7>
Yeah... this.
Heading to the supermarket? .
Heading out here?
Get the Ford Ranger.
The only adventure gear
Built Ford Tough.
Woman:
This is your wake-up call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis,
month after month,
the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
HUMIRA can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
that contributes
to joint pain
and irreversible damage.
VO: HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and so
fatal infections
includinulosis,
and cancers, including
Serious and so
lymphoma, have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Woman:
Help stop the clock
on further irreversible
joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here. Right now.
HUMIRA.
When did you see the sign?
Right here. Right now.
When I needed to
jumpstart sales.
Build attendance for an event.
Help people find their way.
FASTSIGNS designed new
directional signage.
...and got them back on track.
Get started at fastsigns.com.
♪ ♪
>> Bret: U.S. CUSTOMS AND
BORDER PATROL IS REPORTING WHAT
IT SAYS ARE UNPRECEDENTED
NUMBERS AND ILLEGAL IMMIGRANT
APPREHENSIONS.
THE RIO GRANDE VALLEY SECTOR
SAYS A DESK AFTER MORE THAN
164,000 PEOPLE SO FAR THIS YEAR.
THAT SURPASSES THE TOTAL FOR ALL
OF LAST YEAR.
BORDER PATROL AGENTS ARREST AN
AVERAGE OF MORE THAN 1100 PEOPLE
PER DAY.
THE LEADER OF AN ANTI-ILLEGAL
IMMIGRATION MILITIA IS IN
CUSTODY TONIGHT IN NEW MEXICO.
HIS ARREST COMES AS HIS GROUP
OBTAINED SEVERAL MIGRANTS, AND
THAT VIDEO WENT VIRAL.
JONATHAN HUNT TELLS US WHERE
THINGS STAND TONIGHT.
>> LEAVE ME ALONE.
TO SPEAK OF THE UNITED
CONSTITUTIONAL PATRIOTS AS THEY
CALL THEMSELVES HAVE MADE NO
SECRET OF THEIR WORK, POSTING
VIDEOS ON FACEBOOK, SHOWING
THEIR MEMBERS DRESSED IN
MILITARY FATIGUES, SOME WEARING
LAW ENFORCEMENT STYLE BADGES
READING FEDERAL REFUGEE -- THEY
HAVE BEEN FINDING MIGRANTS AND
LOCATIONS DETAINING THEM UNTIL
REAL BORDER PATROL AGENTS
ARRIVED, THEY HAVE BEEN
CONDEMNED BY THE ACLU, CUSTOMS R
PROTECTION, AND THE
GOVERNOR OF NEW MEXICO.
OVER THE WEEKEND IN A JOINT FBI
POLICE OPERATION, THE LEADER
69-YEAR-OLD LARRY MITCHELL
HOPKINS WAS ARRESTED NEAR SUMLIN
PARK, NEW MEXICO.
NEAR WHERE THE GROUP HAS SET UP
WHAT IT CALLS A BASE CAMP.
>> A FRIEND OF OURS FROM THE
POLICE DEPARTMENT CAME UP AND
SAID, CAN YOU TALK TO US FOR A
LITTLE BIT?
THAT WAS THAT.
AND THEN WE HEARD THAT HE WAS
ARRESTED, WE DID NOT KNOW WHAT
FOR WHAT ABOUT.
>> HE WAS ARRESTED FOR BEING A
FELON IN POSSESSION OF FIREARMS
AND AMMUNITION, THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL CALLED HIM A
"DANGEROUS FELON, WHO SHOULD NOT
BE ARMED AROUND CHILDREN AND
FAMILIES ADDING THAT THE ARREST
BY THE FBI SAYS THAT THE RULE OF
LAW SHOULD BE IN TRAINED ARMED
OFFICIALS, NOT ARMED VIGILANTES.
THEY ANNOUNCED AN EMERGENCY ON
THE FACEBOOK PAGE YESTERDAY
SAYING THAT PAYPAL AND GO FIND
ME HAVE SUSPENDED THE ACCOUNTS,
AND ASKING FOR DONATIONS TO BE
SENT BY CHECK.
>> MAKING HIS FIRST COURT
APPEARANCE TODAY, FBI DOCUMENTS
FILED WITH THE COURT DETAILED
HIS LONG CRIMINAL HISTORY AND
HIS GROUP'S ALLEGED PLANS TO
ASSASSINATE PRESIDENT OBAMA AND
HILLARY CLINTON.
>> Bret: JONATHAN, THANK YOU.
WE TOLD YOU EARLIER THAT THE 19
STRONG PRESIDENTIAL FIELD HAS
HAD A TOUGH TIME COMING TO ANY
CONSENSUS WHETHER PURSUING
IMPEACHMENT PER PRESIDENT TRUMP.
TONIGHT ONE THING, JUST ABOUT
ALL OF THEM AND OF FACT MOST
AMERICANS AGREE ON.
CORRESPONDENT ALICIA CUNEO IN
DENVER ON THE LEGALIZATION OF
MARIJUANA.
>> ONCE POLITICAL KRYPTONITE
LEGALIZING MARIJUANA IS A KEY
ISSUE THAT DEMOCRATIC POLITICAL
HOPEFULS ARE HOPING TO ADD
STREET CREDIT TO THEIR BASE.
>> THIS IS A LITMUS TEST AS ALL
OF THE DIFFERENT CANDIDATES ARE
COMPETING TO BE PERCEIVED AS THE
MOST AGGRESSIVE CANDIDATE.
>> FINDING 60% OF VOTERS FAVORED
LEGALIZING MARIJUANA.
THREE CANDIDATES PUSHING FOR
LEGALIZATION.
>> WHILE, IN CASE YOU HAVE NOT
NOTICED, A LOT OF PEOPLE ON OUR
SIDE ARE DOING JUST THAT.
>> DO NOT TO TALK TO ME ABOUT
LEGALIZING MARIJUANA UNLESS IN
THE SAME BREATH YOU TALK TO ME
ABOUT EXPUNGING THE RECORDS OF
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE.
>> CORY BOOKER HAS A PLAN TO
LEGALIZE MARIJUANA AT THE
FEDERAL LEVEL, 2020
CONTENDERS ARE SPONSORS.
>> HAVE YOU EVER SMOKED?
>> I HAVE.
I THINK IT GIVES A LOT OF PEOPLE
LEGAL IN TEN STATES IN THE
DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA.
FORMER COLORADO GOVERNOR OVERSAW
THE NATION'S FIRST EXPERIMENT TO
LEGALIZE EVEN THOUGH HE
INITIALLY OPPOSED IT.
OF THEES INASSIFICAT
FEDERAL PRO
BANKING.
>> IF YOU WANT TO ARREST FOR
HOW YOU GET CORRUPTION AND
CREATE A GENERATION OF
GANGSTERS, MAKE SURE A NEW
INDUSTRY IS OFF OF CASH.
>> WITH A FOCUS ON DRUGS AT THE
BORDER, PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS BEEN
HANDS OFF AS A CANDIDAYS
IT SHOULD BE UP TO THE STATES.
DISTANCE AND THE MESSAGE HAS
HARD AND.
>>  HE STRONGLY BELIEVES THAT WE
HAVE TO ENFORCE FEDERAL LAW.
>> THIS WILL BE AN ISSUE FOR THE
DEMOCRATS AND THEY WILL TRY TO
USE THIS AGAINST TRUMP AND THE
GENERAL, BUT THEY DO NOT THINK
THAT IT WILL WORK VERY WELL.
>> WHEREVER THEY LAND, THERE IS
MAJOR MONEY ON THE LINE, AND
COLORADO ALONE, MARIJUANA
BUSINESS REPORTED $1.5 BILLION
IN SALES LAST YEAR.
>> Bret: THANK YOU.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS HE IS NOT
WORRIED ABOUT IMPEACHMENT AT
ALL.
CONFERENCE CALL OF HOUSE
DEMOCRATS JUST WRAPPED UP.
AND THE PANEL WILL WEIGH IN ON
EVERYTHING.
STAY WITH US.
♪ ♪
pay as much for insurance...
As not safe drivers!
AH!
That was a stunt driver.
That's why Esurance has
this DriveSense® app.
The safer you drive,
the more you save.
Don't worry, I'm not
using my phone
and talking to a
camera while driving...
I'm being
towed.
By the way,
I'm actually
a safe driver.
I'm just pretending to
be a not safe driver.
Cool.
Bye Dennis Quaid!
When insurance is affordable,
it's surprisingly painless.
Diaper Duty.
It's not the highlight
of fatherhood.
But I'd rather be here
with my little man
than anywhere with migraine.
"I am here."
And I aim to say that more.
Aimovig...
a preventive treatment for
migraine in adults...
reduces the number of monthly
migraine days.
For some, that number can be cut
in half or more.
The most common side effects
are pain,
redness or swelling at the
injection site and constipation.
Aim to be there more.
Talk to your doctor
about Aimovig.
(Mom VO) It's easy to shrink
into your own little world.
Especially these days.
(Dad) I think it's here.
(Mom VO) Especially at this age.
(Big sister) Where are we going?
(Mom VO) It's a big, beautiful
world out there.
(Little sister) Woah...
(Big sister) Wow. See that?
(Mom VO) Sometimes you just need
a little help seeing it.
(VO) Presenting the all-new
three-row Subaru Ascent.
Love is now bigger than ever.
My reputation was
trashed online,
I felt completely helpless.
My entire career and business
were in jeopardy.
I called Reputation Defender.
They were able to restore
my good name.
If you're under attack,
I recommend calling
Reputation Defender.
And consider joining their
groundbreaking campaign
to give every American the
right to remove old,
inaccurate search results by
going to righttobeforgotten.org.
If you have search results that
are wrong or unfair,
call Reputation Defender
at 1-877-866-8555.
INITIATE IMPEACHMENTTHE HOUSE
PROCEEDINGS.
>> THEY STILL HAVE NOT FOUND THE
MESSAGE, SO THEIR ONLY OPTION IS
TO ATTACK THIS PRESIDENT.
>> SOME OF THIS WOULD BE
IMPEACHABLE, YES.
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE WOULD BE
IMPEACHABLE.
>> THIS IS HOW IT STARTED.
>> IT IS A VERY DIFFICULT
DECISION, WE WILL HAVE A CAUCUS
ABOUT THIS OVER THE NEXT COUPLE
OF WEEKS TO TRY TO FIGURE
WHEST COURSE IS.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT, MR. PRESIDENT  ?
>> Bret: EASTER EGG ROLL WITH
IMPEACHMENT QUESTIONS CAME AFTER
THE PRESIDENT, ONLY HIGH CRIMES
AND MISDEMEANORS CAN LEAD TO
IMPEACHMENT, NO COLLUSION, NO
OBSTRUCTION, SO YOU CAN'T
IMPEACH.
IT WAS THE DEMOCRATS THAT
COMMITTED THE CRIMES, AND ANGER
REPUBLICAN PRESIDENT, TABLES ARE
TURNING ON THE WITCH HUNT.
YOU HEARD ADAM SCHIFF MENTIONED
THAT THEY WERE GOING TO CAUCUS
ABOUT THE
WAY FORWARD.
HOUSE DEMOCRATS DID HAVE A
CONFERENCE CALL THIS EVENING.
IT JUST OPENED UP -- WRAPPED UP
MOMENTS AGO.
TWO SOURCES ARE SAYING THAT
FINANCIAL SERVICES CHAIRWOMAN
MAXINE WATERS IS PUSHING FOR
IMPEACHMENT.
SHE IS SAYING THAT SHE IS NOT
PUSHING HER COLLEAGUES TO JOIN
HER.
SHE IS SIMPLY SAYING WHAT SHE
THINKS, MAKING HER VIEWS KNOWN.
TO THE HIGHEST PROFILE DEMOCRAT
URGING IMPEACHMENT, BUT NOT
REALLY A SURPRISE, SHE HAS BEEN
ORDERING IMPEACHMENT BEFORE THE
MUELLER REPORT.
LET'S BRING IN THE PANEL, CHRIS
STIREWALT, SUSAN PAGE,
WASHINGTON BUREAU CHIEF AT USA
TODAY, AND ALSO THE AUTHOR OF
THE NEW BOOK, THE MATRIARCH
"BARBARA BUSH IN THE MAKING OF
THE DYNASTY" DEBUTING NUMBER
THREE ON "THE NEW YORK TIMES"
LIST, AND CHIEF CORRESPONDENT OF
THE "WASHINGTON EXAMINER,"
SUSAN, CONGRATULATIONS ON THE
BOOK.
AT THE MEETING, IT IS A
CONUNDRUM.
I TALKED TO BRIT HUME EARLIER IN
THE CHAUFFEUR DEMOCRATS ON THE
WAY CONSIDERING WHAT THE MUELLER
REPORT DID NOT FIND PREY TO
SPEAK ON DEMOCRATS ARE DIVIDED
ON THE QUESTION OF WHETHER
IMPEACHMENT MAKES SENSE.
DEMOCRATS ARE UNITED IN THINKING
THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS DONE
THINGS THAT THEY DO NOT LIKE.
THEY ARE AT ODDS WITH THE OATH
THAT HE TOOK AN OFFICE, BUT THE
LEADERSHIP OF THE HOUSE
DEMOCRATS INCLUDING NANCY PELOSI
CLEARLY DO NOT WANT TO GO DOWN
THE IMPEACHMENT ROAD.
WHAT THEY ARE GOING TO DO IS
HAVE INVESTIGATIONS FOR THE
IMPEACHMENT MEANING, YOU LOOK AT
WHAT THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE HAS ALREADY LINED UP
TESTIMONY BY JOHN McCANN, THE
FORMER WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL, BY
BILL BARR, BY ROBERT MUELLER,
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL, ALL OF
THOSE ARE SCHEDULED FOR MAY, SO
THEY MAY NOT CALL IT
IMPEACHMENT, BUT THEY WILL HAVE
INVESTIGATIONS.
>> Bret: THEY ARE CLEARLY
DIVIDED RIGHT NOW, BUT I THINK,
AND THEY HAVE GOTTEN ALL EXCITED
ABOUT ALL OF THE DETAILS THAT
HAVE COME OUT ESPECIALLY ABOUT
ALLEGED OBSTRUCTION IN THE
MUELLER REPORT, BUT THE FACT IS
THAT IT IS GOING TO MAKE IT MORE
DIFFICULT FOR THEM.
ONE, IT DID NOT FIND COLLUSION
OR CONSPIRACY OR COORDINATION,
AND TWO, IT DID NOT FIND THAT
THE INVESTIGATION WAS ACTUALLY
OBSTRUCTED.
IT FOUND THAT THE PRESIDENT
ORDERED PEOPLE TO PERFORM
OBSTRUCTIVE ACTS AND THEY SAID
"NO."
HE BACKED DOWN AND THAT DID NOT
HAPPEN, DEMOCRATS WILL BE
ACCUSING THE PRESIDENT OF TRYING
UNSUCCESSFULLY TO OBSTRUCT AN
INVESTIGATION INTO SOMETHING
THAT DID NOT HAPPEN.
AND I THINK THAT POLITICALLY
THAT IS THE CASE WHERE THE
PRESIDENT CAN MAKE A STRONG
DEFENSE.
>> Bret: OUR FRIEND JONATHAN
TURLEY, LAW PROFESSOR WROTE A
COLUMN IN THE HILL SAYING
DESPITE IDENTIFYING TEN
TROUBLING EPISODES THAT COULD BE
DEFINED AS OBSTRUCTION, MUELLER
WILL NOT SAY WITH CONFIDENCE
THAT HE ACTED WITH INTENT.
FINDING EVIDENCE THAT HE WANTED
TO LEND THE SCOPE OF THE
INVESTIGATION, BUT THAT IS NOT
NECESSARILY INTENT, EVEN THE
BEST WORD PRESIDENT TRUMP
SEEKING TO FIRE MUELLER WAS
JUSTIFIED AS BASED ON THE FEAR
OF THE CONTRACT OF INTEREST LIKE
IMPEACHABLE ACTS, SHOWING OF
INTENT, NOT IN AN ARRAY OF
IMPOSSIBLE ATTEMPT.
AND WHAT WE ARE GETTING AT IS IF
THE HOUSE DEMOCRATS WHO MOVE
FORWARD, IT GETS STICKY, BECAUSE
HE WOULD THINK THAT THE SENATE
AND REPUBLICAN CONTROL IS NOT
GOING TO CONVICT ANYWAY.
>> SENATE MAJORITY IS ALL THAT
IS NEEDED TO BRING THE CHARGES,
THAT IS THE INDICTMENT, BUT YOU
NEED A SUPER MAJORITY,
TWO-THIRDS TO CONVICT HIM
REMOVE.
THE DEMOCRATS KNOW THAT THAT
WILL NOT HAPPEN AND NOT ANYTIME
SOON.
IMPEACHMENT IS A POLITICAL
QUESTION, NOT A LEGAL ONE.
AND FOR ALL OF THE GOOD WORK OF
ALL OF THE LEGAL SCHOLARS IN THE
WORLD, IT COMES DOWN TO A
FUNDAMENTAL POLITICAL QUESTION.
THE QUESTION HERE IS WHAT THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE, COUNTENANCE AND
IMPEACHMENT.
AND THEY PROBABLY KNOW THAT
THERE IS NOTHING THAT ANYONE WHO
VOTED FOR DONALD TRUMP IN 2016
COULD HAVE READ IN THE MUELLER
REPORT, SCSI AS MUCH OF IT WAS,
THAT WAS NOT ALREADY BAKED INTO
THE
FIGURING OF DONALD TRUMP, HE DID
NOT RUN AS POPE FRANCIS IN 2016S
STUFF AND HIS CHARACTER BEFORE
HE RAN, THAT'S WHY IT IS A
NONSTARTER.
>> Bret: THE DECISION THAT
DEMOCRATS WILL MAKE WILL BE THE
INSPECTOR GENERAL'S REPORT,
OTHER INVESTIGATIONS INTO THE
EARLY PART OF THE INVESTIGATION
WHICH COULD ILLUMINATE SOME
ASPECTS OF THAT.
>> THE MUELLER REPORT MAKES IT
LESS LIKELY THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
FACES IMPEACHMENT, BUT
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S TAX RETURN
INTO THE ORGANIZATION'S BUSINESS
PRACTICES INTO WHAT HAS HAPPENED
THE VARIOUS AGENCIES AROUND TOWN
THAT HAVE HAD VERY LITTLE
OVERSIGHT IN THE FIRST TWO YEARS
OF THE ADMINISTRATION.
NOTHING IS GOING TO STOP THAT.
>> Bret: IS IMPEACHMENT THE
LITMUS TEST OF THE GREEN NEW
DEAL OR A MEDICARE FOR ALL IN
2020?
>> THAT IS THE TASK THAT
NANCY PELOSI IS TRYING TO
NAVIGATE.
YOU SAW HER ADDRESS A COLLEAGUE
IN THE CONFERENCE CALL MAKING
THE CASE AND AGREEING THAT
DONALD TRUMP HAS DONE THINGS
THAT MAKE HIM UNFIT FOR OFFICE,
BUT AGREEING THAT THEY NEED TO
PURSUE THE TRUTH BUT SAYING THAT
YOU CAN DO THAT WITH
INVESTIGATIONS THAT ARE SHORT OF
IMPEACHMENT.
>> ONE LAST THING THAT THE
LEADERSHIP IS AWARE OF, THE
TIMING OF THIS WILL BE CRAZY.
IF THE DEMOCRATS START NOW, IT
WILL TAKE A WILD TO REV UP THE
IMPEACHMENT REGIME, AND WHEN
THEY GET GOING, WE WILL BE SMACK
IN THE MIDDLE OF A PRESIDENTIAL
ELECTION CAMPAIGN WHERE THE EPG
IS RUNNING FOR REELECTION, WHEN
BILL CLINTON WAS IMPEACHED, IT
WAS IN '98 AND '99 AFTER HE HAD
BEEN REELECTED, AND THAT WAS
AFTER HE HAD BEEN REELECTED IN
1972, NIXON.
DOING THIS IN THE MIDDLE OF A
CAMPAIGN WOULD PUT THE WHOLE
PROCESS ON STEROIDS.
IT'S CRAZY ENOUGH TO BEGIN WITH.
THE LEADERSHIP IS VERY WORRIED
ABOUT JUST THE UNPREDICTABLE
ASPECT OF THAT.
>> Bret: AND THE COUNTERPUNCH
ARE IN CHIEF WHO CLEARLY WILL
NOT HOLD BACK.
PANEL, THANK YOU.
MASSACRE, THE TERRORIST ATTACK
THERE.
AND THE IRANIAN OIL WAVES.
♪ ♪
. Strength that lasts. o@o@
You'll ask...
What pain?
With Advil.
♪
Incomparable design
makes it beautiful.
State of the art technology
makes it brilliant.
The visionary Lexus NX.
Lease the 2019 NX 300 for
$359 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
Feel the clarity of
non-drowsy Claritin
and relief from
Symptoms caused
by over
200 indoor
and outdoor
allergens.
Like those
from buddy.
Because stuffed
animals
e clearly no substitute
for real ones.
Feel the clarity.
And Live Claritin clear.
I'M ALEX TREBEK,
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
AND LOOKING TO BUY LIFE
INSURANCE ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
-THE THREE P'S?
-WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE,
AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 65 AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH
FOR YOU TOO.
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE #1 MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN,
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE
IS GUARANTEED.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
♪ ♪
>> TODAY I'M ANNOUNCING THAT WE
WILL NO LONGER GRANT ANY
EXEMPTIONS.
WE ARE GOING TO ZERO.
WE ARE GOING TO ZERO ACROSS THE
BOARD TO.
>> IF WE CAN TRULY STOP RAINING
AND EXPORTS,/  TALKING MAYBE
1,000,000.542 MILLION BARRELS
PER DAY THAT NOW HAS TO BE
FILLED BY SOMEBODY.
>> IT IS NOT ABOUT SUPPLY, IT IS
ABOUT POLICY.
IT IS ABOUT WHETHER THOSE
COUNTRIES WOULD BE WILLING TO GO
ALONG WITH THIS DEMAND.
>> THIS IS THE BIGGEST LEVERAGE
WE HAVE, IF YOU WHEN THEY SEEK A
CHANGE IN BEHAVIOR, YOU HAVE TO
SHOW SERIOUSNESS OF PURPOSE ON
THE OIL.
>> Bret: THE U.S. IS PUTTING
THE BOOTS ON THE NECK OF IRAN
WHEN IT COMES TO FINANCES, THAT
IS SQUEEZING THE OIL REVENUES.
IF YOU LOOK, THE WAIVERS HAVE
BEEN CUT OFF, LAST NOVEMBER THE
U.S. GAVE EIGHT COUNTRIES FAVORS
TO CONTINUE TO BUY IRANIAN OIL,
THEY HAVE ELIMINATED THAT
IMPORT, GREECE, ITALY, AND
TAIWAN, FIVE REMAINING COUNTRIES
HAVE THESE WAIVERS, CHINA,
INDIA, TURKEY, SOUTH KOREA, AS
OF TONIGHT THAT STOPS.
BACK WITH THE PANEL, BIG DEAL?
>> I THINK IT IS, THAT SHOWS
THAT THE TERM ADMINISTRATION IS
REALLY, REALLY SERIOUS ABOUT
THIS, NOT GIVING ANY MORE
WAIVERS.
IN THE WAKE OF PULLING OUT OF
THE IRANIAN NUCLEAR DEAL, MAKING
SURE THAT THEY DO NOT HAVE THESE
MILLIONS AND MILLIONS OF DOLLARS
TO SPEND DESTABILIZING THE
MIDDLE EAST.
SO I THINK THAT EVERYBODY SHOULD
PROBABLY BELIEVE MIKE POMPEO
WHEN HE SAYS THIS.
>> Bret: TURKEY HAD SOME
PUSHBACK PUBLICLY, BUT OTHER
THAN THAN THAT, SILENCE FROM THE
OTHER COUNTRIES.
>> I THINK THAT JAPAN IS
PROBABLY GOING TO GO ALONG WITH
THIS, ONE OF THE CLOSEST ALLIES,
TURKEY, NATO, WE GET TO OTHER
COUNTRIES, WHAT ARE WE WILLING
TO DO?
HOW FAR WE WILLING TO    TO GO O
ENFORCE ON CHINA?
HOW FAR WILL WE GO TO ENFORCE?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT AS A STATEMENT
OF RESOLVE AS A PUBLIC STATEMENT
TO SAY, THIS IS HAPPENING AND WE
ARE GOING THERE, THAT IS A
PRETTY BOLD MOVE.
>> THE QUESTION IS WHAT IS THE
BACK END?
LET'S SAY THAT THE REGIME
CRUMBLES, WHAT HAPPENS?
WE DON'T KNOW.
>> WE DON'T KNOW, AND WE DON'T
KNOW HOW THIS WILL GO, BUT IT IS
COMPLETELY CONSISTENT WITH WHAT
THE ADMINISTRATION HAS SAID.
NONE OF THESE COUNTRIES SHOULD
BE A SURPRISE THAT THESE WAIVERS
ARE EXPIRING.
AND IT IS NO MORE SIGN THE
PRESIDENT COMPETENT IN DOING
WHAT HE WANTS TO DO AND
DISREGARDING WHAT SOME STATE
TIES WITH FOREIGN POLICY EXPERTS
CONCERNED WITH BEING ISOLATED
FROM ALLIES OR THE IMPACT ON
CHINA, ON OTHER ISSUES.
I THINK THAT ON FOREIGN POLICY
HE IS INCREASINGLY WILLING TO DO
WHAT HE SAID HE WAS GOING TO DO.
>> Bret: IN PART BECAUSE U.S.
ENERGY AND OUR ABILITY TO
PRODUCE OUR OWN OIL AND NATURAL
GAS.
JUST BECAUSE THERE IS THAT, AND
THE PRESIDENT WEEDED OUT THAT
THE SAUDI ARABIANS, AND
EVERYBODY WILL KEEP THE SUPPLY
UP, BUT TO WHAT SUSAN SAID, I
THINK THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
MORE CONFIDENT ABOUT THIS,
BECAUSE THERE ARE OTHER TIMES
THAT HE HAS BEEN TOLD THAT THE
WORLD WOULD END IF YOU DID
SOMETHING, AND HE DID IT AND THE
WORLD DID NOT END, I'M THINKINGT
MOVING U.S. EMBASSY IN JERUSALEM
WHERE THERE WERE PREDICTIONS OF
DIRE CONSEQUENCES THAT WOULD
OCCUR, YET HE DID IT.
IT HAS BEEN FINE.
AND THAT IS THE VIEW ON THISOO
PRAY >> Bret: HERE IS THE
PRESIDENT ON THE SRI LANKAN
ATTACK.
>> WHAT A TERRIBLE, TERRIBLE
THIN
UNTHINKABLE.
A LONG TIME AND PEOPLE DO NOT
WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT, IT IS A
TERRIBLE THING, I JUST SPOKE
WITH THE PRIME MINIS
I SPOKE WITH THE VARIOUS
GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS, AND WE ARE
WORKING WITH SRI LANKA, BUT THAT
IS A TERRIBLE THING.
>> Bret: 300 DEAD, IN THE
SUICIDE ATTACKS ON CHRISTIANS.
SPECIFIC, AND IT WAS KNOWN BY
NUMEROUS INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES.
>> THERE COULD BE A LINK TO
ISIS, OR LARGER EFFORTS ACROSS
THE GLOBE AND ALL OF THESE
THINGS.
THIS IS WHAT WE WORRY ABOUT.
THIS IS THE CONCERN THAT EVERY
AMERICAN HAS, BECAUSE IT COULD
COME HERE.
AND FOR AMERICAN CHRISTIANS,
THIS IS A SOMBER MOMENT.
>> Bret: IF YOU LOOK AT THE
CHART OF CHRISTIANS KILLED
WORLDWIDE FOR FAITH-RELATED
REASONS, YOU CAN SEE THE
NUMBERS, THEY ARE STAGGERING,
BUT 2018 THERE ARE 4,136, SUSAN?
>> AN EASTER DAY BOMBING IS
PRETTY HORRIFIC, IT IS A
REMINDER THAT EVEN THOUGH ISIS
HAS LOST ITS TERRITORY, ISIS AND
SIMILAR RADICAL ISLAMIC GROUPS
REMAIN A TERRIBLE THREAT.
AND IT WAS TURNING OUT TO BE
VERY SOPHISTICATED BOMBS, THEY
MANAGED ALL OF THE HAVOC WITH
SEVEN SUICIDE BOMBERS.
IN SOME HELP FROM INTERNATIONAL
TERRORIST GROUPS.
SPEAK OF THOSE ARE THE TWO BIG
THINGS TO BE CONCERNED ABOUT,
THE OBVIOUS COORDINATION,
SEVERAL BOMBS ON OPPOSITE SIDES
OF THE COUNTRY GOING OFF
SIMULTANEOUSLY, AND THE FACT
THAT THE INTELLIGENCE SERVICES
HAD BEEN WARNED ABOUT THIS QUITA
WHILE AGO, WHY DID THEY NOT TAKE
SOME SORT OF ACTION ON THIS?
>> Bret: WE WILL CONTINUE TO
FOLLOW, PANEL, THANK YOU.
WHEN WE COME BACK, GOOD NEWS
FROM THE MEN AND WOMEN IN BLUE.
♪ ♪
I don't keep track of regrets.
And I don't add up the years.
But what I do count on...
is BOOST®.
Delicious BOOST®
High Protein Nutritional Drink
has 20 grams of protein,
with 26 essential
vitamins and minerals.
BOOST® High Protein.
Look for savings on BOOST®
in your Sunday paper.
♪ ♪
Plants capture CO2.
What if other kinds of plants
ca■technologyçgçgçgçg■g@
that captured carbon like trees
we could help lower emissions.
Carbon Capture is important
technology -
and experts agree.
That's why we're working on ways
to improve it.
So plants...
can be a little more...
like plants.■C■
♪ LiMu Emu & Doug ♪
■Ñ■■y
What do all these people
have in common, Limu?
[ paper rustling ]
Exactly, nothing.
They're completely
different people,
that's why they
need customized
Car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need!
[ gargling ]
[ coins hitting the desk ]
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done
it again, LiMu.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>> FINALLY TONIGHT WE THOUGHT WE
WOULD POINT OUT GOOD DEEDS FROM
POLICE OFFICERS AROUND THE
COUNTRY.
R DAN PATTERSON THAT MADE
5-YEAR-OLD ISAIAH HALL'S DAY BY
BRINGING HIM McDONALD'S AFTER HE
CALLED 911 ASKING FOR SOMETHING.
OFFICER PATTERSON TAUGHT THE BOY
WHEN EMERGENCY CALLS SHOULD BE
MADE AND NOT MADE.
BUT HE GOT HIS McDONALD'S.
NEXT, OFFICER ROGER JAMALLIS IN
ST. LOUIS.
HE PULLED OVER A YOUNG MAN FOR
DRIVING A CAR WITH EXPIRED
PLATES AND DAMAGED WINDOW.
HE WAS ON HIS WAY TO A JOB
INTERVIEW.
HE THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO GET A
TICKET.
INSTEAD, HE GOT A RIDE THANKS TO
THE OFFICER, HE GOT THE JOB.
A DOZEN OFFICERS IN KANSAS CITY,
KANSAS WENT TO EXTRA MILE TO  AT
LEXIE TOOK THE BIKE FOR A TEST
DRIVE, ALMOST FELL OFF.
THERE WAS AN OFFICER THERE TO
CATCH HIM.
GOOD DEEDS OF OFFICERS AROUND
THE COUNTRY TONIGHT.
THANKS