>> Shannon: A DRAMATIC RESCUE
CAUGHT ON CAMERA, 221-YEAR-OLD
KAYAKING WHEN THEY CAPSIZED IN
CHILLY WATERS.
IT WAS HOURS BEFORE CALIFORNIA
HIGHWAY PATROL HELICOPTER
FINALLY FOUND THEM.
RESCUERS CREDITING THE
LIFEJACKETS THEY HAD ON SAYING
THEY PLAYED A VITAL ROLE TO KEEP
THEM■ ALIVE.
>> WE ARE GLAD YOU SPENT YOUR
EVENING WITH US, GOOD NIGHT FROM
WASHINGTON.
I AM SHANNON BREAM.
♪ ♪
>> Tucker: GOOD EVENING AND
WELCOME TO
"TUCKER CARLSON TONIGHT."
THE HOLIEST DAY OF THE CHRISTIAN
CALENDAR TURNED TO TRAGEDY
YESTERDAY AS YOU KNOW I
SRI LANKA.
THE COORDINATED ATTACK, SUICIDE
BOMBERS STRUCK THREE CATHOLIC
CHURCHES AND■ HOTELS THE66
AT LEAST 290 PEOPLE WERE
MURDERED AND HUNDREDS MORE WERE
INJURE
THE ATTACKERSAF WERE AFFILIATED
WITH A LOCAL TERROR GROUP.
THERE WERE RADICAL MUSLIMS,
THEIR MOTIVES WERE R■■
THEIR TARGETS WERE CHRISTIANS.
NONE OF THAT IS SPECULATION.
IT IS TRUE.
MAYBE BECAUSE IT IS SO TRUE AND
SO OBVIOUSLY TRUE NOBODY IN
BVAUTHORITY WANTED TO SAY IT OUT
LOUD SO INSTEAD THEY WENT TO
GREAT LENGTHS TO AVOID THE CLEAR
LANGUAGE.
THE ATTACKS ON EASTER WORSHIPERS
ARE AN ATTACK ON HUMANITY
TWEETED BARACK OBAMA.
HILLARY CLINTON USED THE SAME
PHRASE.
"I AM PRAYING FOR EVERYONE
AFFECTED BY THE HORRIFIC ATTACK
AND TRAVELERS IN SRI LANKA.
EASTER WORSHIPERS."
WHY DON'T YOU SAY CHRISTIANS?
NOBODY WORSHIPS EASTER.
THERE IS A REASON, OF COURSE,
EUPHEMISMS ARE NEVER ACTUAL.
OUR LEADERS BELIEVE CHRISTIANS
ARE THE PROBLEMS, THE DANGEROUS
ONES WHO CAN'T BE TRUSTED.
TELL THEM THE TRUTH AND THEY
MIGHT GO CRAZYZYND AND ORGANIZEA
NEW CRUSADE.
MARCH ON JERUSALEM.
YOU NEVER KNOW WITH CHRISTIANS.
JUST TONIGHT THE
"THE WASHINGTON POST" RAN A
STORY WITH THIS HEADLINE,
"SRI LANKA CHURCH BOMBING ANGER
IN WEST."
TOIVE TO BE A NAZI
BE UPSET ABOUT CHURCH BOMBINGS.
THAT IS WHY OUR LEADERS IGNORE
THE PERSECUTIONS OF CHRISTIANS
AROUND T WHEN U.S.FFCY CONTRIBUT
PERSECUTION. O
AND IT DOES, THEY SAY NOTHING
ABOUT IT.
LESS THAN 20 YEARS AFTER WE
OVERTHREW SADDAM HUSSEIN, THREE
QUARTERS OF IRAQ'S ONE THRIVING
CHRISTIAN POPULATION IS GONE.
THEY HAVE EITHER BEEN MURDEREDEY
ISIS IN SOME CASES
ORVE BEEN DRIVEN OUT OF
THE P COUNTRY AS REFUGEES.
IN SYRIA CHRISTIANS HAVE LIVED
UNDER GENERATIONS UNDER
PROTECTI OF THE BASHARAL-ASSAD .
TRUE, IT IS TRUE AND YOU CAN
TALK TO THE HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF CHRISTIANS WHO FLED
THE COUNTRY SINCE THE U.S. BEGAN
SUPPORTING THE DISMISSAL BASHAR
AL-ASSAD.TH
IF YOU WANT TO KNOW DETAILS.
NOBODY IN THE MEDIA EVER ASKS
THEIR OPINION AND NOBODY CARES.
SO MANY OF OURAT
ALLIES IN THE MIDDLE EAST,
COUNTRIES THAT RECEIVE BILLIONS
REPRESS CHRISTIANITY.
AFGHANISTAN FOR EXAMPLE RECEIVES
BILLIONS FROM US EVERY YEAR.
FOWHY?
SO WE CAN TURN IT INTO BELGIUM.
RIGHT NOW IN AFGHANISTAN
CONVERTING TO CHRISTIANITY
CARRIES A DEATH SENTENCE IF YOU
ARE MUSLIM, THE SAME IS TRU■■■Uñ
BOTH COUNTRIES BACKED B
UNITED STATES.
IN EGYPT CONVERSION IS
RESTRICTED ALTHOUGH IT DOESN'T
CARRY DEATH, POLLS SHOW THAT
MOST OF THE PUBLIC WISHES IT
DID.
WHERE IS OUR STATE DEPARTMENT?
THEY SPEND A LOT OF TIME LOOKING
AT THE HUMAN RIGHTS OFON PEOPLEN
COUNTRIES WE CAN PRONOUNCE.
THEY IGNORE IT.
ONE WAS THE LAST TIME THE U.S.
PUSHED ANOTHER COUNTRY TO
COUNTRY CHRISTIANS BETTER?
IN SOME CASES IT'S PRETTY EASY
TO DO THAT, WE COULD DEMAND THAT
ON US IMPLEMENT FULL FREEDOM OF
RELIGION BEFORE WE GIVE THEM ANY
MORE USAID.
WHY WOULD WE DO THAT?
BECAUSE WE ARE AFRAID OF BEING
CRITICIZED BY
"THE WASHINGTON POST."
THE FOUNDER OF PULLIAM AND THE
AUTHOR OF A RADICAL, MY JOURNEY
OUT OF EXTREMISM.
AND HE JOINS US TONIGHT.
WE ARE HAPPY TO HAVE YOU.
EXPLAIN IF THE THINKING BEHIND
NOT JUST BEING STRAIGHTFORWARD
WITH THE PUBLIC ABOUT AN EVENT
LIKE THE ONE WE SAW YESTERDAY IN
SRI LANKA.
>> I AM A MUSLIM AND I EXPRESS
MY DEEPEST CONDOLENCES TO
CHRISTIANS AROUND THE WORLD DUE
TO THIS AND AFTER THIS HORRIFIC
TERRORIST ATTACK IN SRI LANKA
THAT CLAIMED NEARLY 300 LIVES.
MANY DON'T'S KNOW THIS, BUT I AM
MARRIED TO ANAL AMERICAN FROM A
CATHOLIC FAMIL'S WHY
IT'S SO IMPORTANT FOR ME
PERSONALLY TO MAKE THIS POINT.
UNFORTUNATELY, OUR LEADERS AND
IN PARTICULAR SOME OF THE
POLITICAL LEADERS THAT YOU HAVE
NAMED OUR SUFFERING FROM WHAT I
BELIEVE IS AN INTELLECTUAL AND
MORAL RETREAT FROM OUR
ENLIGHTENMENT VALUES AND ALSO A
LEVEL OF POLITICAL CYNICISM
INVOLVED HERE AS WELL.
THE INTELLECTUAL SIDE FOR, A
WHILE NOW WHETHER WHEN
BARACK OBAMA WAS PRESIDENT OR
EVEN AFTER THEY HAVE BEEN
UNABLE --
I CALL IT THE VOLDEMORT EFFECT.
THEY HAVE BEEN UNABLE TO NAME
EXTREMISM BY NAME AND JIHADIST
TERRORISM, A VIOLENT
MANIFESTATION BECAUSE I
GENUINELY BELIEVEIC THAT A BIGGR
THREAT TO THEIR POLITICAL
PERSPECTIVE IS WHITE SUPREMACYCY
AND FAR RIGHT EXTREMISM AND THEN
OF COURSE THERE IS THE PRAGMATIC
POLITICAL SIDE OF THINGS.
THEY ARE PANDERING TO A CERTAIN
VOTE BASE AND I THINK THAT BY
NAMING THESE THINGS EVEN IF THEY
WANTED TO, IT WOULD TROUBLE WITH
THEIR BASE AND TOT HOW I
OPERATE AND I THINK ANY HUMAN
BEING SHOULD OPERATE.
WHAT HAPPENED IN NEW ZEALAND WAS
A TERRORLA ATTACK AND WHAT HAS
HAPPENED IN SRI LANKA IS A
JIHADIST HOTTEST TERROR ATTACK
AND IT MOVES US ALL TO SPEAK
PLAINLY ABOUT THIS SO
WE CAN ADDRESS THESE PROBLEMS.
>> Tucker: WHAT DOES THAT SAY
ABOUT HOW THEY FEEL ABOUT THEIR
OWN POPULATIONS AND THE SUPPOSED
DEMOCRACY?
THEY CAN'T BE STRAIGHTFORWARD.
HAN AMERICANS CAN'T
IDEA OF KNOWING THAT ISLAMIC
EXTREMISTS DID THIS AND STILL,
NOT HATE ALL MUSLIMS?
THEY HAVE A LOW OPINION OF THEIR
OWN POPULATION.
>> "THE WASHINGTON POST" THAT
YOU REFERENCED, THEY FEAR A FAR
RIGHT BACKLASH AND I HAVE READ
THE ARTICLE IN QUESTION AND IT
SELECTS ONLY THOSE WHO ARE FROM
THE RIGHT OF THE POLITICAL
SPECTRUM AND THEIR REACTIONS TO
THE TERROR ATTACK IN SRI LANKA.
IT IS VERY EASY TO DO THAT BY
THE WAY, LAZY BAIT JOURNALISM.
I ADVISED FELLOW JOURNALIST NOTE
TO DO THAT.
AFTER THE NEW ZEALAND TERROR
ATTACK I COULD HAVE SAID THAT
THE EAST FEARS A BACKLASH FROM
JIHADISTS AND I COULD HAVE HAND
SELECTED AND HAD ONLY REACTIONS
TO THE NEW ZEALAND ATTACK TO TRY
TO PORTRAY THE FACT THAT ONLY
THE JIHADISTS AND ISLAMISTS WERE
UPSET.
IT IS A DISHONEST WAY TO SHOW
THAT.
I THINK SADLY TOO MANY PEOPLE
PLAY POLITICS WITH TRAGEDY AND
THEY ALLOW FOR THEIR OWN
FRAMEWORK OF THEIR OWN BIAS TO
INFLUENCE HOW THEY VIEW HUMAN
TRAGEDY AND THEN THEY USE THAT
TO PEDDLE THEIR OWN POLITICAL
NARRATIVE.
WEke SHOULD ALL BE AS CONSISTENT
AS POSSIBLE.
>> Tucker: AND STOP LYING,
THAT MAKES EVERYONE CYNICAL AND
IT CAUSES THE YOU FEAR.
THANK YOU.
A WISE VOICE AS ALWAYS.
NINA SHEA IS A RELIGIOUS FREEDOM
EXPERT AT THE HUDSON INSTITUTE
HERE IN WASHINGTON AND SHE JOINS
US TONIGHT.
I WOULD SAY THAT IT UNDERSELLS
WHAT YOU DO.
YOU ARE THE MOST CONSISTENT AND
THE MOST KNOWLEDGEABLE EXPERTS
ON THE PERSECUTION OF CHRISTIANS
AROUND THE WORLD.
>> THANK YOU THANK YOU FOR
FOCUSING ON THIS ISSUE.
>> Tucker: GIVE US AN OVERVIEW
OF THE PICTURE?
>> LET ME JUST SAY THAT FIRST
THIS■ES JUST TO
THOSE NS WHO WERE
ATTACKED AND KILLED OVER THE■n
WEEKEND OVER EASTER WEEKEN
IT WSAGE THAIS
BASICALLY A WAR ON CHRISTIA/p/pp
FROM A CERTAIN SEGMENT OF THE
MUSLATION.
THE MUSLIM EXTREMIST POPULATION.
OVER THE LAST DECADE IN PLACES
LIKE EGYPT WHES WHO
WAS AN ANALYST THERE, HE
ESTIMATES THERE ARE ABOUT 500
CHURCH ATTACKS IN THE LAST
COUPLE OF YEARS.
THESE OCCURRED ON PALM SUNDAY, A
COORDINATED ATTACK A COUPLE OFOF
YEARS AGO.
ON CHRISTIANS IN DECEMBER AROUND
CHRISTMAS TIME AT THE SEAT OF
ST. MARK'S CATHEDRAL.
I WAS JUST THERE AND SAW THAT
SITE.
IT IS HEARTBREAKING.
IT HAPPENS QUITE OFTEN.
>> Tucker: WHERE IS
UNITED STATES STATE DEPARTMENT?
>> IT IS NOT SAYING ENOUGH.
THE PRESIDENT OF EGYPT TENDS TO
GO AFTER THE BOMBING ATTACKS
THAT ISIS DOES BUT THERE ARE
EXTREMIST MUSLIMS IN THE LOCAL
NEIGHBORHOOD THAT ARE ATTACKING
CHURCHES WITH IMPUNITY AND HAVE
BEEN FOR QUITE A WHILE A WHILE
IN EGYPT.HI
ABOUT 10% OF THE POPULATIONS ARE
CHRISTIANS THERE.
NIGERIA ESTIMATED 900 CHURCH
ATTACKS IN A FIVE YEAR PERIOD.
THESE ARE AGAIN HAPPENING ONóóóV
CHRISTMAS, ON EASTER, IT DOESN'T
MATTER WHAT STRIPE OF
CHRISTIANITY YOU ARE, ACROSS THE
BOARD.
>> Tucker: POWERFUL CHURCHES
FOR THE UNITED STATES, RICH
CHURCH IS FOR SURE, POWERFUL
CLERGYMEN, I DON'T HEAR THIS
ISSUE ADDRESSED.
WHY IS THAT?
>> I DON'T THINK PEOPLE ARE
AWARE OF IT.
SOME OF THEM ARE AFRAID THAT
THEY WILL GET RETRIBUTION BY THE
EXTREMISTS, BUT THEY DON'T TALK
ABOUT ITLK IN THOSE COUNTRIES.
THERE ARE VARIED REASONS WHY
PEOPLE DON'T TALK ABOUT IT BUT
THE SHORT TERM SOLUTION IS
SECURITY.
WE NEED TO PROMOTE THAT.
IN FACT THE UNITED STATES DID
GIVE A QUIET WARNING TO
SRI LANKA THAT CHURCHES WOULD BE
■@■@F THEY DIDN'T ACT.
AND THEY DID NOT HEED IT.ST
WE NEED TO ELEVATE THIS.
>> Tucker: WE HAVE GIVEN
BILLIONS TO AFGHANISTAN BUT YOUN
■■HINKNK THAT WOULD AT LEAST
BUY US, THE MAJORITY CHRISTIAN
COUNTRY A CHANGE IN THE LAW THAT
WOULD MAKE IT A DEATH PENALTY
OFFENSE TO CONVERT..
WHY WOULD WE FUND A GOVERNMENT
LIKE THAT?
>> WHILE WE HAD OUR TROOPS THERE
THEY BROKE THE LEASE IN THE LAST
CHURCH OF THE COD CLOSED
IT.
WE DON'T.
WE SELL OURSELVES SHORT.
WE DON'T EVER DIVIDE CHRISTIANS.
WE ALWAYS HAVE A HIGHER PRIORITY
REGARDING TARIFFS BUT WE DON'T
UNDERSTAND THERE IS A LINK
BETWEEN THE TWO.
THE WEAKNESS OF THOSE CHRISTIANS
FEEDS THIS.
IT MAKES THEM A SOFT TARGET.
THE GOVERNMENT'S DON'T FEEL LIKE
ANY PRESSURE COMING FROM US.
THEY FEEL PRESSURE COMING FROM
ONE SIDE, THE EXTREMISTS.
>> Tucker: THAT IS SUCH A
SMART POINT, THERE IS A LINK.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THE MUELLER REPORT CAME OUT LAST
WEEK, NO COLLUSION, NO CRIME,
DEMOCRATS ARE STILL TALKING
ABOUT IMPEACHMENT.
WILL THEY DO IT?
OWWE TALKED TO SOMEONE WHO MIGHT
KNOW THE ANSWER, AFTER THE
BREAK.
♪ ♪
■■■■■37■■/■■■■O■O■O■■O■C%C%■s
>> Tucker: DEMOCRA HAVE NOW
HAD A FULL WEEKEND TO READ THE
MUELLER REPORT TO LOVINGLY SAVOR
EVERY WORD, TO DIGEST IT.■
DOES IT HAVE, AND THIS IS THE
KEY QUESTION, FROM DATE■
KEY QUESTION,TI THE CRIMES WE HE
BEEN HEARING ABOUT FOR TWO YEARS
THAT WOULD JUSTIFY HIRING A
SPECIAL PROSECUTOR AND AFTER
HAVING DONE THAT IT WOULD
JUSTIFY IMPEACHMENT?
DEMOCRATS ARE GOING TO HAVE TO
MAKE A DECISION ON THAT.
LAWMAKERS AND PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES ARE IGNORING THE■
REPORTS ACTUAL CONCLUSION THAT
LOOKS LIKE THEY MAY BE DEMANDING
IMPEACHMENT ANYWAY.
>> I THINK WHEN YOU LOOK AT THIS
REPORT YOU CAN SEE THAT THERE IS
ENOUGH INFORMATION THERE, NOT
ONLY ON OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE
BUT ALSO ON COLLUSION OR
CONSPIRACY WHATEVER YOU WANT TO
CALL IT TO MOVE FORWARD WITH
IMPEACHMENT ON THIS PRESIDENT.
>> WE ARE NOT FARTHER AWAY FROM
IMPEACHMENT.
IF ANYTHING YOU READ THIS
DOCUMENT AND YOU FIGURE OUT HOW
WE WILL HOLD THIS PRESIDENT
ACCOUNTABLE.
>> DO THINK THIS IS IMPEACHABLE?
>> YEAH, I DO.D
>> I THINK IT WOULD BE PERFECTLY
REASONABLE FOR THEM TO OPEN UP
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS.
>> IT IS TIME FOR IMPEACHMENT.
>> Tucker: YOU HEARD IT.
IT IS TIME FOR IMPEACHMENT.
HE JOINS US, THANK YOU FOR
COMING ON.
WHEN DOES IMPEACHMENT START?
>> I HAVE GONE BOTH WAYS MYSELF
AND HERE'S WHAT WE KNOW FROM THE
MUELLER REPORT.
PEOPLE CAN MAKE FUN OF IT, WE
KNOW INDISPUTABLY THAT
DONALD TRUMP WON WITH THE HELP
OF A HOSTILE FOREIGN POWER AND
THAT HE KNEW HE WAS GETTING THAT
HELP AND HE ACTUALLY SOLICITED
THE HELP.
HE DID NOTHING TO ALERT
AUTHORITIES TO IT AND HE HAS
DONE ZERO TO KEEP IT FROM
HAPPENING AGAIN.
>> Tucker: YOU ANSWERED YOUR
OWN QUESTION.
WHEN IS THAT STARTING?
WE HAVE BEEN WAITING FOR THREE
YEARS TO TAKE IT AWAY FROM HIM,.
THE NOMINATION AND THEN THE
ELECTORAL COLLEGE AND THEN WE
WILL IMPEACH HIM.
YEARS HAVE GONE BY AND WE HAVE
THE REPORT, LET'S STOP MESSING
AROUND.
ONE IS IMPEACHMENT?
>> YOU ONLY GO FORWARD WITH ANY
GRAND JURY WITH AN IMPEACHMENT
WHICH IS THE ACCUSATION, NOT A
TRIAL BY VIRTUE OF HAVING THE
EVIDENCE AND THATTH WILL BE HAVG
DON JR.. AND ROGER STONE COME
FORWARD.
>> Tucker: IT IS NOT LIKE WE
WILL LEARN STORY CHANGING FACTS
FROM THE REDUCTIONS.
>> THERE WERE A LOT OF THINGS
THAT MUELLER DIDN'T GET.
>> Tucker: I'M BEING
DISINGENUOUS, WE BOTH KNOW HE IS
NOT BEING IMPEACHED,WE BOTH KNOW
THAT DEMOCRATS WANT TO HAVE IT
BOTH WAYS WHERE THEY CAN PRETENS
IT'S SERIOUS ENOUGH TO MERIT
IMPEACHMENT BUT THEY DON'T WANT
THAT BECAUSE THEY WILL LOSE AND
BE PUNISHED BY VOTERS.
>> I DISAGREE WITH THAT.
THE DEMOCRATS WON FIVE SEATS,
GEORGE W BUSH WROTE THAT ABOUT
HOW HE WILL HAVE A CLEANER
WHITE HOUSE AND I WOULD SAY
JIMMY CARTER TO A CERTAIN EXTENT
WITH THE NIXON IMPEACHMENT.
>> Tucker: WHY NOT DO IT?
>> THE QUESTION ON WHETHER IT IS
A RIGHT OR WRONG THING.
>> Tucker: YOU CAN'T TELL THE
PUBLIC FOR THREE YEARS THAT THE
GUY IS A NAZI.
HE'S A TRADER.
HE'S WORKING WITH A HOSTILE
POWER.
EVERY SINGLE DAY FOR YEARS WE
HAVE HEARD THIS BUT WE CAN'T
IMPEACH HIM BECAUSE WE CAN'T
CONVINCE THE SENATE?
>> THAT AS A WHOLE ANOTHER
THING.
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS THE
HOUSE WILL BRING THESE PEOPLE IN
AND MAYBE THEY WILL GET ACCESS
TO ALL OF THESE BOXES OF
EVIDENCE AND MAYBE NOT AND MAYBE
THEY HAVE TO BASICALLY BRING
EVERYBODY ELSE UNDER OATH.
IS IT A WASTE OF TIME?
IF YOU TAKE THE WATERGATE
HEARINGS AND IF YOU THINK THEY
WERE A WASTE OF TIME THEN YOU
WOULD THINK THESE ARE TOO.
MOST PEOPLE IN THE PUBLIC,
PERSONALLY I WAS.
IS WATERGATE AND I DON'T THIS
K IN THE
HAPPEN AT ALL AND I THINK WHAT
DEMOCRATS A ARE ACTUA
MISSING AN OPPORTUNITY TO AT
LEAST THINK THROUGH HOW TO HELP
THE COUNTRY IN SOME TANGIBLE WAY
BEFORE THEY GET BEAT INEVITABLY
ORE IN A PRESIDENTIAL
RACE.
THAT IS WHERE WE ARE GOING.
>> WORSE THAN WATERGATE IN A
SENSE THAT THERE IS NOT JUST A
HOSTILE FOREIGN POWER BUT
DONALD TRUMP LAUGHING ABOUT IT,
IT IS ALMOST AN INDICATION FOR
-- INVITATION FOR
CHINA AND NORTH KOREA TO DO THE
SAME THING.
>> Tucker: RUSSIA IS NOT A
THREAT TO US.
>> IF YOU THINK THEIR COUNTRIES
THAT ARE THERE AND LOOKING THE
OTHER WAY DO NOTHING, WHAT IS
GOING TO STOP CHINA?
>> Tucker: THE MOST ANTI-CHINA
PRESIDENT IS IN CHARGE OF THAT?
>> HE IS INVITING IT.
NEXT TIME HELP HIM IF IT WORKS
FOR HIM.
>> Tucker: AMAZING.
HERMAN CAIN A CANDIDATE TO SERVE
UNDER THE FEDERAL RESERVE, HE
DIDN'T WITHDRAW BECAUSE HE WAS
INCOMPETENT ORR  CYNICAL BECAUSE
HE WAS SHOWN AS A UNSUITABLE
PICK, HE DROPPED HIS BID BECAUSE
HE WAS BLACKMAILED.
INTO DOING THAT.
ATTORNEY GLORIA TEAMED UP AND
SAID THEY WOULD EXPOSE HIM TO
PUBLIC HUMILIATION UNLESS HE
WITHDREW HIS NAME.
>> IF ASKED AT THE UNITED STATES
SENATE BANKING COMMITTEE
HEARING, HE WILL ALSO BE WILLING
HTO IDENTIFY CERTAIN PARTS OF S
BODY TO COOPERATE HER TESTIMONY.
THIS TESTIMONYRA WILL NOT BE
NECESSARY IF MR. CAIN WITHDRAWS
HIS NAME FROM THE VETTING B
PROCESS AND OR THE PRESIDENT
DECIDES NOT TO FORMALLY NOMINATE
HIM.
>> Tucker: JASON NICHOLS IS A
PROFESSOR OF AFRICAN-AMERICAN
STUDIES AT MARYLAND.
THANK YOU FOR COMING ON.
YOU SAID PRETTY CLEARLY YOU ARE
NOT A FAN OF HERMAN CAIN
AND YOU DON'T THINK HE SHOULD
HAVE GOTTEN THIS JOB?
YOU DON'T SUPPORT HIM.
>> I DO NOT.
>> Tucker: WHATT DO YOU THINK
GIVEN THAT
>>AS ABOUT H
CUT OR SOMETHG, THE RN TAKE WHD
AND I BELIEVE GLORIA ALLRED HAS
DONE SOME POSITIVE THINGS IN HER
CAREER IN TERMS OF GIVING VOICE
TO PEOPLE WHO ARE VOICELESS BY
DOINGCA THINGS LIKE THAT ACTUALY
UNDERMINES THE MOVEMENT,
UNDERMINES WHEN PEOPLE LIKE
TARANA BURKE ARE DOING WORK TO
GIVE VOICE TO WOMEN.Ñn
qr:OOKS LKMAIL.
WE WILL SHOW, WE WILL DEPICT
YOUR GENITALS IF YOU DON'T DO
WHAT WE WANT YOU TO DOçk
PULL YOUR NAME AND HE CLEARLY
CAVED UNDERSTANDABLY.
DO YOU WANT TO LIVE IN A SOCIETY
WHERE PEOPLE WANT TO BE
BLACKMAILED LIKE THAT?
>> I AGREE WITH THAT.
THERE WERE CREDIBLE ALLEGATIONS
AGAINST HIM SO WE HAVE TO STATE
THAT.
>> Tucker: ALLEGATIONS OF
WHAT?E
>> A WOMAN SAID THAT HERMAN CAIN
HAD DONE SOME THINGS THAT WERE
REALLY SEXUAL MISCONDUCT.AT
OF BUT THE CASE --
>> Tucker: THE ONE I READ
ABOUT SAID IT WAS CONSENSUAL?
>> THAT IS THE PROBLEM.
WHEN YOU CONFLATE SOMETHING THAT
IS CONSENSUAL WITH ABUSE, YOU
.INFLATE THAT AND THAT IS THE BG
PROBLEM HERE.■g■g■1
WHAT THEY DID TO HERMAN CAIN IN
THAT REGARD SAYING THAT WE WILL
EXPOSE WHAT YOUR GENITALS LOOK
LIKE, EITHER WAY, THAT THEY
WOULD THAT IS TOTALLY WRONG.
I WOULD AGREE WITH YOU THAT
GLORIA ALLRED IS ACTUALLY
UNDERMINING THIS AND I CAN TELL
YOU THAT I ACTUALLY BELIEVE THAT
THIS COULD BE USED AGAINST WOMEN
IN THE FUTURE.
>> Tucker: YOU THINK?
>> THIS COULD BE VERY
PROBLEMATIC.
THIS IS ACTUALLY GOING TO HURT
WOMEN.
MEN DON'T GET BODY SHAMED LIKE
WOMEN DO.
SOME DUDE WHO HAD AN AFFAIR WITH
KAMALA HARRIS OR LIZ WARREN IS
GOING TO SAY, KIND OF THREATEN
HER IN THE SAME WAY AND THIS IS
REALLY PROBLEMATIC.
AGAIN, THE OTHER THING --
>> Tucker: IT HURTS MEN WHICH
IS EVERY BIT AS BAD AS HURTING
WOMEN BECAUSE HUMAN BEINGS ARE
EQUAL.
>> I WILL SAY ONE OTHER THING.
IT SEEMS UNFORTUNATELY FOR THE
RIGHT PRICE YOU HAVE SOMEONE
LIKE LISA BLOOM WAS IS THE
DAUGHTER WHO SUPPORTED HARVEY
WEINSTEIN AND WAS TALKING ABOUT
PUTTING THINGS OUT AGAINST ROSE
AND OTHER PEOPLE WHO WERE
FIGHTING FOR THE ME TOO MOVEMENT
THAT WAS SO POSITIVE.
SHE WAS ACTUALLY SUPPORTING
HARVEY WEINSTEIN FOR A WHILE.
>> Tucker: SHE WAS GETTING
PAID.
OBVIOUSLY.
>> IT IS REALLY TROUBLING.
>> Tucker: WHY DO WE TAKE THEM
SERIOUSLY?
THEY WOULDN'T EXIST WITHOUT THE
MEDIA GIVING THEM AIRTIME AND
THEY SAY THEY ARE ADVOCATES FOR
WOMEN.
THEY ARE ADVOCATES FOR
THEMSELVES.
THEY ARE TOTALLY DISHONEST.
>> I WANT TO BELIEVE THERE IS A
SOME SINCERITY THERE.
>> Tucker: [LAUGHS]
NEYOU ARE A GOOD MAN.
>> I THINK THEY'RE MAKING A BIG
MISTAKE IN WHAT THEY ARE DOING.
>> Tucker: I DON'T THINK THEY
CARE BUT I ADMIRE YOUR HIGH
HOPES FOR THEM. T
THANK YOU.
A YEAR AGO THE CREEPY PORN
LAWYER WAS TRAVELING ABOARD A
PRIVATE JET THAT WAS HIS, HOW
DID HE AFFORD THAT?
WE KNOW THE ANSWER AND WE WILL
YOU TONIGHT.
PLUS WEAVE FOOTAGE SHOT BY ONE
OF OURHO SHOWS
SHOCKING DETAIL WHAT IS
COUNTRY'S GREATEST CITIES.■■■■■/
♪
■■■"■■■■■■■■■■■■■■    ■■
>> Tucker: THE CREEPY LAWYER
HAS SIMPLE OLD FASHION@ TASTE.
HE IS HAPPIEST INSIDE HIS CNN
STUDIO BUT WHEN HE IS TRAVELING
HE LIKES TO TRAVEL IN STYLE ON
BOARD HIS OWN PRIVATE JET.
HOW CAN HE AFFORD THAT?
LUCRATIVE?
NOT UNLESS YOUR CLIENTS
INCLUDING AN NBA PLAYER
EX-GIRLFRIEND.
LEXUS GARDNER HAD HIRED
THE LAWYER WAS AIDED IN GETTING
A $3 MILLION SETTLEMENT BUT
ACCORDING TO PROSECUTORS HE
IMMEDIATELY STOLE 2 MILLION FROM
THE SETTLEMENT TO BUY A JET.
THE CLIENT RECEIVED LESS THAN
EIGHT TENTHS OF THAT.
KEEP IN MIND CNN TOLD US HE WAS
A PRESIDENTIAL CONTENDER, MAYBE
HE IS TRYING TO GET USED TO
TRAVELING PRIVATE.
VIRTUALLY EVERYTHING YOU HEAR
REPEATED ON TELEVISION, IF THEY
REPEATED ENOUGHED PROBABLY UNTR.
PORTERS ARE RACISTS.
WE ARE STRONGER THE LESS WE HAVE
IN COMMON THE OTHER PEOPLE,
KENTUCKY HIGH SCHOOLERS,
JOURNALISTS IN D.C. AREIN WARRIS
FOR THE OPPRESSED.
IT IS ALL FAKE.
THESE ARE LIES AND THEY REPEAT
THEM OVER AND OVER AGAIN AND
BECAUSE THE LIES ARE POWER.■[A[[
THEY DECIDED TO FIGHT BACK IN
THE MOST RADICAL WAY BY TELLING
THE TRUTH NO MATTER WHAT PEOPLE
THINK ABOUT IT.
A PIECE FOR "THE NEW YORK POST,"
NO MATTER WHAT THEY TELL YOU,
MAN CANNOT GIVE BIRTH, ONLY
WOMEN CAN.
US TONIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR COMING ON.OI
I GUESS THIS IS AN OBVIOUS POINT
BUT HOW MUCH THE WORLD HAS
CHANGED IN FIVE YEARS WHERE
WOMEN GIVE BIRTH AND MEN DON'T
IS CONSIDERED SOME RADICAL OR
HATEFUL STATEMENT?
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
>> IT WAS A CONCERTED MOVEMENT
IN THE TRANS-MOVEMENT WHICH HAS
SOUGHT TO RADICALLY REDEFINE THE
RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN WHAT EACH
REALLY IS.
THE FACT THAT MEN AND WOMEN HAVE
DIFFERENT CHROMOSOMES TILL THE
POINT, THEY ARE DIFFERENT AND WE
KNOW THAT.
BECAUSE IT WAS A TINY MINORITY
OF PEOPLE WHO FEEL DISCOMFORT IN
THEIR BODIES, THEY HAVE SET OUT
ON THIS TOTALITARIAN EFFORT TO
ASK EACH OF US TO SAY, MEN CAN
HAVE BABIES AND WOMEN CAN HAVE
PENIS'S.
IT IS A BIZARRE IDEA BUT WE HAVE
GONE TO THIS POINT AND AS YOU
SAID, IF YOU DESCRIBE FOR US --
>> Tucker: THAT IS THE THING.
I THINK MOST AMERICANS ARE HAPPY
TO LET PEOPLE BELIEVE WHATEVER
THEY WANT T TO BELIEVE.
I LIVE IN MY OWN FANTASY HALF
THE TIME, IT IS FINE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THE IDEA THAT YOU GET TO IMPOSE
YOUR FANTASY ON OTHER PEOPLE AND
THEN GET THEM FIRED OR CRUSHED
IF THEY WON'T PLAY ALONG, THAT
IS TOTALITARIAN.
>> IT IS KIND OF LIKE WINSTON AT
THE END OF 1984 WHERE YOU HAVE
TO SAY THAT HE IS HOLDING UP IN
TORTURE AND HOLDING UP FIVE
FINGERS WHEN HE IS ONLY HOLDING
UP FOUR.
IF YOU SAY FIVE HE WILL GIVE YOU
PAIN.
WE ARE NOT BEING DISPATCHED TO
THE GULAGS BUT THE PAIN COMES IN
PRESSURE WITH YOUR CAREER,
PRESSURE ON YOUR PUBLIC PRESENCE
IF YOU TRY TO SPEAK UP AGAINST
THIS. T
AT THE BOTTOM OF THIS IS THE
DESIRE FOR RADICAL AUTONOMY.
AUTONOMY TO THE LEVEL OF I CAN
ALSO REDEFINE WHAT IT MEANS TO
BE A MAN OR WOMAN.
WE DEFINE AUTONOMY THAT WAY, FOR
ME TO BE ABLE TO EXPERIENCE MY
FULLEST AUTONOMY YOU HAVE TO SAY
YOUR NAME IS SABRINA AND THAT I
AM A WOMAN AND VICE VERSA.
IT IS THIS IDEA OF AUTONOMY
PUSHED FOR SUCH AN EXTENT WHERE
IT BECOMES AUTHORITARIAN.
>> Tucker: IT ELIMINATES MY
AUTONOMY.
I HAVY ALONG.
BY THE WAY, I DON'T THINK WE ARE
OVERSTATING THE EXTENT OF THE
REPRESSION.
YOU AND I HAVE THE ONLY TWO JOBS
WHERE WE CAN HAVE THIS JOB IN
PUBLIC WITHOUT GETTING FIRED.
IF YOU WORKED AT SOME INVESTMENT
BANK, SOME INSURANCE COMPANY,
YOU WILL GET FIRED FOR SAYING
THIS.
>> YOU ABSOLUTELY WOULD.
IT INCLUDES LOTS OF WOMEN, WE
NOW HAVE A LOT OF WOMEN'S
ATHLETICS BEING DOMINATED BY
PEOPLE WHO HAVE THE RAW PHYSICAL
CAPABILITIES OF MALE BODIES
BECAUSE THEY HAVE THAT.
NOW THROUGH THISOT IDEA OF MEN
BEING ABLE TO BECOME PREGNANT,
WE ARE REFRAMING PREGNANCY.
SOMETHING SINCE TIME AND
MEMORIAL HAVE BEEN BOUND UP FOR
WHAT IT MEANS TO BE A WOMAN.
SOMETHINGOU YOU AND I COULD NEVR
EXPERIENCE AND NOW THAT IS
BECOMING A MALE EXPERIENCE.
>> Tucker: I DON'T KNOW HOW
THAT EMPOWERS WOMEN AND WHERE
ARE AMERICA'S BIOLOGY TEACHERS
WHEN YOU NEED THEM?
I'M NOT TAKING A POLITICAL
POSITION HERE, BUT HERE ARE THE
FACTS.
>> THERE ARE A FEW.
AGAIN, THEY ARE DISTANT VOICES.
THE GREAT PSYCHOLOGIST OF HIS
GENERATION AT JOHNS HOPKINS IS
THERE.
THE IDEOLOGICAL MOVEMENT HAS SO
MADE INROAD IN THE MEDICAL
PROFESSION WHERE WITH
PROFESSIONS WITH THE DOMINANT
CONSENSUS, THE BIOLOGICAL SEX,
THE REPRODUCTIVE ORGANS THAT YOU
ARE BORN WITH IS NOT THE BASIS
FOR DETERMINING YOUR GENDER.TH
IT IS NOT JUST IN THE PUBLIC
SPHERE, AMONG PSYCHIATRISTS AND
SO FORTH.
THIS HAS BECOME THE NORM AND IT
IS YOUR POWER POLITICS.
>> Tucker: ONLY RICH COUNTRIES
CAN AFFORD TO BE THIS DECADENT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
OVERWHELMINGLY SPEAKING OF KIDS,
AMERICANS WANT TO HAVE THEM.
THEY WANT TO HAVE MORE CHILDREN
THAN THEY HAVE AND THIS WAS ONE
AO CORE PROBLEMS IN OUR
SOCIETY STEAD OF FIXING
THIS POLITICIANS TELL US WE
SHOULD BRING IN NEW PEOPLE IN
ORDER TO KEEP OUR POPULATION
STABLE.
ELIZABETH WARREN SAID SHE WOULD
BE GIVING A $50,000 STUDENT LOAN
AMNESTY TO ALL COLLEGE GRADS.
HERE'S THEDAO PROPOSAL, WHY NOT
L FORGIVE ALL THE LOANS OFHE
AMERICANS WHO GET MARRIED AND
HAVE KIDS?
IT MIGHT HELP.
WHY IS THAT CRAZY?
THE PRESIDENT OF CONCERNED WOMEN
OF AMERICA.
THANK YOU FOR COMING ON.
MOST AMERICANS WANT TO HAVE MORE
CHILDREN THAN THEY CAN AFFORD.
WHY IS THIS NOT THE BASIC
EYPROMISE EVERY POLITICIAN RUNNG
FOR EVERY OFFICE IS MAKING?
IF ELECTED I WILL HELP YOU HAVE
AS MANY KIDS AS YOU WANT.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW THAT WORKS
OUT ECONOMICALLY BUT WE HAVE TOI
ADDRESS THIS.
IT HAS IMPLICATIONS FOR ELDERLY,
SOCIAL SECURITY AND NEW MARKETS
FORR CORPORATIONS.
IF WE HAVE LESS CHILDREN, IF THE
POPULATION CONTINUES TO DECLINE,
WE ARE NOT AT REPLACEMENT RATE.
THAT IS 2.1 AT 1.7.
WE WILL NOT RETIRE NEARLY AS
SOON AND WE WILL HAVE TO WORK
HARDER.
AMERICAN WOMEN SAY THE VAST
MAJORITY WANT TO HAVE CHILDREN
AND WOMEN WITH MINOR CHILDREN,
60% SAY THEY WANT TO SPEND MORE
TIME WITH THEM.
IF THEY HAD THEIR IDEAL
SITUATION, 60% WOULD ONLY WORKTH
PART TIME.
19% WOULD STAY AT HOME WITH
THEIR KIDS.
>> Tucker: WHY WOULDN'T A
POLITICAL PARTY SAY HERE IS A
HUGE GROUP OF PEOPLE WHO WANT
SOMETHING DEEPLY, WHY DON'T WE
HELP THEM PROVIDE IT?
>> THE REPUBLICAN PARTY NEEDS TO
STEP UP AND LEAD ON THIS.
WE ARE TRYING P TO DO MORE,
SOMEONE WORKED WITH IVANKA TRUMP
TO WORK ON THAT.
TEXT CREDIT FROM $1,000 TO
$2,000.
IT SHOULD BE MORE.
WE ARE TALKING THROUGH POLICIES
NOW THAT WOULD ALLOW WOMAN TO
DIP INTO THEIR SOCIAL SECURITY
AHEAD OF TIME WHILE THEY ARE AT
THEIR LITTLE BABIES AND THENTH
JUST DELAY GETTING IT LATER OR
LESS ON THE BACK END.
WE HAVE TO REALLY THINK THROUGH
THIS.
WE NEED TO TALK TO CORPORATIONS.
WE WANT MORE T POSSIBILITY ASAL
WOMEN.
>> Tucker: SHOULD WE BE
SHOOTING FOR LIKE SIX YEARS?
>> WE NEED TO FIND PROPOSALS
THAT GIVE MORE FLEXIBILITY TO
WOMANNG AND THAT IS A BROADER
CONVERSATION INCLUDING CORPORATE
AMERICA AND REMOVING ALL THE
MANY REGULATIONS THAT STOP US■■
■■FROM HAVING THIS INDUSTRY.
BECAUSE OF HIGH TAXES ON THE
WORLD WE LIVE IN WE ARE A TWO
INCOME FAMILY IS THE NORM IN
MOST PEOPLE FEEL LIKE THEY NEED
THAT EXTRA INCOME.
MANY WOMEN WANT TO WORK AT SOME
LEVEL.
LET'S HELP THEM BE FLEXIBLE AND
LET'S THINK OF POLICIES THAT
GIVE THEM THE MAXIMUM AMOUNT OF
TIME THAT THEY WANT TO BE AT
HOME WITH THEIR KIDS OR DADLE
WANTS TO BE AT HOME WITH THE
KIDS.
>> Tucker: I DON'T KNOW WHY IT
NEVER OCCURS TO ANYONE.
THERE ARE LECTURES ON THE
SOCIALISM OR YOU CAN BE AN
ENTREPRENEUR, HOW ABOUT I WANT
TO RAISE MY KIDS?
WHY IS THD?
>> I TALK TO THEM AND ALL THE
TIME AND THEY SAY I AM JUST A
MOM.
YOU HAVE TO CHANGE THAT.
THERE IS NO SUCH THING AS JUST A
MOM.
THAT IS THE MOST IMPORTANT JOB
AND THE HARDEST JOB I'VE HAD.
>> Tucker: THERE ARE NINE
UNHAPPY PEOPLE WHO WRITE OUR
SOCIAL POLICY.
NO MORE LISTENING TO THEM.
PSALMS
KIDS ARE GIFT FROM THE LORD.D.
>> Tucker: FACEBOOK KNOWS MORE
ABOUT YOU THAN YOUR FRIENDS
KNOW, YOUR PARENTS KNOW,
PROBABLY THAT YOU KNOW FROM
YOURSELF.
THEY WANT TO KNOW MORE AND THEY
ARE TRYING TO CONVINCE AMERICA
TO PUT CAMERAS INSIDE THEIR OWN
HOMES.
EVEN THEIR BEDROOMS, IS THAT A
GOOD IDEA?
WE WILL TELL YOU AFTER THE
BREAK.
27 ♪ ♪
>> T
>> Tucker: FACEBOOK IS THE
WORLD'S MOST POPULAR
SOCIAL MEDIA NETWORK.
YOU MIGHT THINK THE WORLD'S
BILLION USERS ARE ITS CUSTOMERS
BUT THEY ARE NOT.
THEY ON THEIR PERSONAL
INFORMATION ARE THE PRODUCT THAT
FACEBOOK SELLS TO ITS
ADVERTISEMENTS.
THAT IS THE ACTUAL ARRANGEMENT.U
IN A CONFERENCE, THEY WANT TO BE
CEO OF FACEBOOK HAS MORE DATA
ABOUT WHAT PEOPLE WANT TO DO
ONLINE THAN ANYONE ELSE IN THE
WORLD.
HE MAY HAVE THE MOST INFORMATION
BUT HE WANTS MORE DATA.
FACEBOOK IS NOW ACCUSING SLICK
ADVERTISEMENTS TO CONVINCE YOU
TO PUT NEW MORE CAMERAS INSIDE
YOUR OWN HOME.
WATCH.
>> HAPPY MOTHER'S DAY.
IT IS SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
YOU HANG OUT WITH THE MOMS OF
OTHER FAMOUS PEOPLE?
SERENA'S MOM, SNOOP DOGG'S MOM,
AM I IN TROUBLE?
>> THERE IS NOTHING WRONG.
COME ON OVER HERE AND LET US
LOOK AT YOU.
>> Tucker: THE FORMER ADVISOR
TO MARK ZUCKERBERG, AND AUTHOR
JOINS US TONIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR COMING ON.
THE LOOKS FROM THAT AT THAT
ILLOGICAL SUCCESSFUL PEOPLE ARE
ALLOWING MARK ZUCKERBERG TO PUT
SURVEILLANCE CAMERAS INSIDE
THEIR HOMES.PL
SHOULD I DO THE SAME?
>> I WOULD NOT RECOMMEND IT, I
WOULD NOT RECOMMEND IT TO ANYONE
WATCHING THAT SHOW.
HE MADE THE POINT CORRECTLY
BEFORE.
FACEBOOK IS THE BUSINESS OF
SURVEILLANCE.
THEY GATHER ALL THE DATA THEY
CAN, NOT JUST THE STUFF THEY PUT
INTO THE SYSTEM BUT THEY TRACK
US.
THEY BUY DATA FROM BANKS AND
CREDITSO CARD PROCESSORS AND THY
BUY IT FROM HEALTH AND WELLNESS
APPLICATIONS AND THEY BUY IT
OUR CELLULAR CARRIERS TO
TELL WHERE WE ARE.
THEY BUY IT ALL SO SO THEY CAN
CREATE A DATA AVATAR FOR US AND
THAT AS YOU SAY, THAT MAKES US
NOT EVEN THE PRODUCT, THE FUEL
FOR THEIR BUSINESS MODEL.
>> Tucker: THAT SEEMS RIGHT.EI
WHY IS IT THAT THERE IS NO
SKEPTICISM IN THE MEDIA ABOUT
THIS OR ANY OF THE OTHER --
KARA SWISHER WHO COVERS
TECHNOLOGY FOR
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" BASICALLY
WRITES PRESS RELEASES.
WHY DOES NOBODY PUSH BACK EVER?
>> TO BE CLEAR THERE IS THE
BEGINNING OF A CHANGE BUT I
THINK YOU ARE RIGHT.
THERE IS A DEFAULT MECHANISM TO
TRUST TECH.
TECHNOLOGY WAS SOMETHING THAT
MADE OUR LIVES BETTER FOR 50
YEARS AND WHAT HAPPENED WITH
FACEBOOK, GOOGLE AND MICROSOFT
AND AMAZON IS THEY HAVE TAKEN
ADVANTAGE OF TRUST AND GOODWILL
AND THEY ARE STARTING TO EXPLOIT
THAT IN A WAY THAT REALLY TAKES
AWAY OUR CHOICE.
THE BUSINESS MODEL THEY HAVE
BUILT IS REALLY, THEY ARE TRYING
TO USE DATA TO TAKE AWAY
UNCERTAINTY FOR ADVERTISERS, THE
PROBLEM ISN'T DOING SO THEY ARE
TAKING AWAY THE CHOICES FOR US
AS THE CONSUMER.
CHOICE IS WHAT IT IS ALL ABOUT.
I THINK THERE IS A PHILOSOPHICAL
DEBATE THAT HAS TO HAPPEN AND AS
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE BEEN AN
IMPORTANT PART OF, I'M TRYING TO
LEAD THIS DEBATE.
THERE ARE TWO POINTS, YOU WANT
TO MAKE THE WORLD MORE EFFICIENT
AND I WANT TO HAVE MORE LIBERTY
AND MORE CHOICES.
I WANT TO SEE WHICH SIDE WINS.
>> Tucker: IN THIS CASE, THIS
AMAZON PRODUCT, IT PIVOTS AROUN■
THE ROOM FOLLOWING YOU AND
SHOOTING FOOTAGE OF WHAT IS
HAPPENING INSIDE YOUR HOME, YOUR
MOST PRIVATE SPACES.PE
THAT IS THE CREEPIEST THING.
WHAT HAPPENS TO THE DAT
HOW DO WE KNOW THAT IS SECURE
AND WILL BE USED AGAINST US?
>> THERE IS NO REASON WE SHOULD
BE TRUSTING AND THE SAME THING
IS TRUE FOR ALEXA AND GOOGLE
HOME AND THE OTHER PRODUCTS THAT
EITHER LISTEN TO YOU OR FILM IN
YOUR HOME.
IT IS CRAZY.
THE NOTION WE WOULD LET ONE OF
THESE THINGS INTO OUR KITCHEN
MUCH LESS OUR OFFICE OR OUR
BEDROOM.
RIGHT NOW THERE ARE NO RULES,
ALL WE HAVE IS THE COMPANIES
WORD.■■
OF COURSE THESE THINGS ARE
VULNERABLE TO HACKING AND THE
PEOPLE WHO WORK THERE ARE
VULNERABLE TO ALL KINDS OF
EXPLOITATION.
MY VIEW IS THAT WE SHOULD STOP
ALL OF THESE THINGS AND PUSH
BACK REALLY HARD.
I WANT TO GO --
I'M SAYING TO EVERY SINGLE
PERSON WHO IS RUNNING
OFFICE, W■■ I'M ON YOUR
AIR, WE SHOULD ASK THE SIMPLE
QUESTION, WHY IS IT LEGAL FOR
THERE TO BE A THIRD PARTY MARKET
WITH OUR PERSONAL DATA, WITHOUT
OUR INVOLVEMENT?
WHY SHOULD THEY TRADE OUR
FINANCIAL DATA, OR HEALTH DATA?
WHY SHOULD GOOGLE BE ALLOWED TO
SCAN OUR EMAILS FOR THEIR
BENEFIT?
IT IS NUTS.
IF THEY WERE THE POSTAL SERVICE
THEY WOULD GET ARRESTED.
I THINK THERE HAS BEEN NO RULES
FOR TOO LONG AND IT'S TIME TO
HAVE SOME RULES.
>> Tucker: THE REAL THREAT IS
VLADIMIR PUTIN AND RUSSIA!
YOU MAKES SOME SOLID POINTS.
GREAT TO SEE YOU.
IT IS EARTH DAY AND INSTEAD OF
CUTTING HIS OWN CARBON
FOOTPRINT, HE HAS A NEW PLAN.
STOP GLASS AND STEEL BUILDINGS?
WHAT DOES IT MEAN WHEN YOU LIVE
IN A COUNTRY THAT CAN TELL YOU
WHAT KIND OF BUILDINGS TO BUILD?
WHAT IS HAPPENING ON THE STREETS
OF LOS ANGELES.
WHEN WE COME BACK.
♪ ♪
H/H■■es■7
>> Tucker: THE FOOTAGE ON YOUR
SCREPICTURE RIGHT THERE,
WAY ONE OF OUR PRODUCERS
LAST WEEK.
WE WERE IN CALIFORNIA ALL WEEK
IN LOS ANGELES, SUPPOSEDLY ONE
OF THE RICHEST CITIES IN THE
WORLD AND IN SOME WAYS IT IS.
BUT THE VIDEO YOU ARE WATCHING
SHOWS SOMETHING ELSE.
CALIFORNIANS MEANDERING POOR,
TRASH FILLED STREETS.
RIGHT IN DOWNTOWN, HOMELESS
ENCAMPMENTS ON THE SIDEWALKS AND
BLANKETING DOWNTOWN L.A.
THE FOOTAGE STARTS AT FIFTH
STREET AND SAN PEDRO AND GOES
WEST.
BLOCK AFTER BLOCK, TENT AFTER
TENT.
THIS IS HOW THE POOR SPENT
EASTER SUNDAY IN CALIFORNIA.
THEY WEREN'T CLUSTERED ON ONE
SINGLE ROAD, IT WASN'T LIKE
SKID ROW.
IT WAS LIKE MANY SKID ROWS.
IT CONTINUED.
IT IS AMERICA'S SECOND LARGEST
CITY.
THE ENCAMPMENTS BEGAN JUST TWO
BLOCKS AWAY FROM LITTLE TOKYO,
ONE OF L.A'S MAJOR TOURIST
DESTINATIONS.W
YOU MIGHT BE WONDERING, WITH SO
MANY PEOPLE PRICED OUT OF LOCAL
HOUSING, FEW PEOPLE ARE
LITERALLY LIVING IN RVs, MILES
OF RVs PARKED ALONG THE
STREET.
THEY ARE IN TENTS, WHY WOULDN'T
LOCAL LEADERS WANT TO SLOW OR
STOP THE FLOW OF NEW ARRIVALS TO
GET PRICES UNDER CONTROL?
TO OPEN UP NEW HOUSING?
THEY ARE DOING THE OPPOSITE.
L.A. IS A SANCTUARY CITY AND AS
SANCTUARY STATE.
THEY WILL DENOUNCE OUR BORDERS
AN ATROCITY AND THAT IS AN
ABOMINATION.
THE POOR IN CALIFORNIA ARE AN
AFTERTHOUGHT, ONE OF THE REASONS
Y THEY ARE MULTIPLYING.
THAT'S WHYGOVERNOR NEWSOM
TRIED TO FIGHT IT, HE FLEW TO
ANOTHER COUNTRY TO DO IT WITH
EL SALVADOR.
THE SAME PEOPLE WHO WANT NO
LIMITS ON PEOPLE WHO ARE MOVING
HERE CAN'T EVEN HOW'S THE PEOPLE
WHO LIVE HERE.
MAY
KNOW, THAT IS A GOOD THING FOROR
THE RECORD.
NEW YORK MAYOR de BLASIO SIZE
UNITED STATES AND ENJOY TAKING
HIS SUV CONVOY ALL OVER THE
CITY, OR HER TAKING A HELICOPTER
O THE GYM.
DON'T WORRY, HE3O3O3O3O PLAN FOR
ABSOLVING HIS OLTRESTRICT THE B.
HE WANTS TO PASS THE GREEN NEW
DEAL WHICH HE SAYS WILL BAN THE
ICONIC SKYSCRAPERS, WATCH THIS.
>> WE WILL BAN THE CLASSIC
GLASS AND STEAL SKYSCRAPERS
WHICH ARE INCREDIBLY
INEFFICIENT.
>> Tucker: MARK STEYN JOINS
US.
I HAVE MIXED FEELINGS.
I'M GOING TO GET IT RIGHT DOWN
ON THE FLOOR
I THINK ALL OF THE CREEPS WHO
DESTROYED THE WORLD'S LANDSCAPE
WITH WORKER HOUSING AND THE T
STEEL, THEY SHOULD BE PUNISHED.
I AM AGAINST STEAL AND GLASS BUT
I DON'T THINK THAT HE WANTS TO
REPLACE IT WITH SOMETHING BETTER
AND88IS MY SUSPICION.
>> I'M WITH YOU.
I AM OPPOSED TO THAT.
ON AESTHETIC GROUNDS.
I AM HORRIFIED AT THE TALK THAT
THEY MIGHT BE I.M. PEI-ING UP
THE NEW 88CATHED
PARIS.S.
I AM WITH YOU.
I'M WITH YOU ON AESTHETIC
GROUNDS BUT I DON'T WANT TO BAN
IT ON CLIMATE GROUNDS, WHICHES I
THINK IS JUST RIDICULOUS, EVEN
ON EARTH DAY.
AFTER WHAT YOU'VE JUST SHOWED
ON THE STREETS OF LOS ANGELES,SA
PERFECT REMINDER THAT CLIMATE
CHANGE IS ESSENTIALLY A BOUTIQUE
ISSUE.
IT IS ALMOST LIKE AN ACCESSORY
FOR WESTERN LIBERAL POLITICIANS
TO FLAUNT HOW MUCH THEY CARE
WHILE ACTUALLY DOING NOTHING
ABOUT THE PEOPLE IN THE
JURISDICTIONS FOR WHICH THEY ARE
RESPONSIBLE.
>> Tucker: IT COULDN'T REALLYFO
BE CLEARER, COULD IT?
WHY WOULDN'T YOU TAKE EARTH DAY
WHICH AT LEAST THEORETICALLY I
SUPPORT.
I LOVE THE OUTDOORS.x
I W FISHING THIS MORNING.WH
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT TO BE
OUTSIDE I THINK.
WHY WOULDN'T YOU TAKE THIS
OPPORTUNITY TO CLEAN UP THE
ACTUAL EARTH?
STARTING HOW ABOUT AT CITY HALL?
WHY WOULDN'T YOU DO THAT?
>> YOU ARE LOOKING AT IT ALL
WRONG.
EARTH DAY IS ABOUT FLYING A
POLITICIAN IN TO DO THE LAST BIT
OF TREE PLANTING THAT SEVERAL OF
HIS STAFF AND AN ENVIRONMENTAL
ACTIVIST HAVE BEEN SPENDING THE
WHOLE DAY WORKING ON.
I LIVE IN A TOWN IN
NEW HAMPSHIRE THAT IS 95%
TREE COVERED.
WE HAVE THE CLIMATE CHANGE
FEVER.
WE NEED TO GET IT BACK TO 98% OR
THE PLANET WILL DIE.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE THAT 3% WENT
I THINK THEY WERE ALL USED TO
PRINT TRANSCRIPTS OF THE MOTHER
REPORT
I THINK THEY WERE ALL USED TO
PRINT TRANSCRIPTS OF THE MUELLER
REPORT.
THAT IS WHAT EARTH DAY IS ABOUT.
DOING SOMETHING ABOUT THE FILTH
IN YOUR OWN CITY.
IT GOES BACK TO THE WAY
LABOR DAY HAS BEEN TRANSFORMED.
RALABOR DAY WAS PARTLY, IN ITS
ORIGINS, ABOUT THE ORDER AND
CLEANLINESS THAT MAN HAS IMPOSED
ON A WILD ENVIRONMENT AND AS YOU
SEE ON THE STREETS OF
LOS ANGELES, EVEN THAT HAS BEEN
RETURNED TO A PRIMITIVE AND
BRUTISH STATE.
>> Tucker: WHAT DO YOU THINK
THE PEOPLE WHO STARTED AMERICA'S
CONSERVATION MOVEMENT, JOHN MUIR
FOR EXAMPLE OR TEDDY ROOSEVELT,
WHO PROTECTED MILLIONS OF ACRES,
WHAT WOULD THEY MAKE OF BILL
de BLASIO'S VARIETY OF
ENVIRONMENTALISM WHERE YOU NEVER
GO OUTSIDE?
>> I THINK THAT IS WHERE THE
WHOLE BIT ABOUT HIM TRAVELING BT
SUV AND EVERYTHING COMES IN.
I THINK THEY WOULD SEE IT AS A
CLASS THING.
IN OTHER WORDS, WHAT WE HAVE
SEEN IN THE LAST 150 YEARS HAS
BEEN THE DEMOCRATIZATION OF
MOBILITY.
THE THINGS YOU HAD TO BE A
COND SON OF A GRAND DUKE TO
DO, LIKE TRAVEL WILDLY, ARE NOW
AVAILABLE TO EVERYONE.
LEONARDO DiCAPRIO AND AL GORE
THINK, NO, IT IS JUST THOSE GUYS
WHO NEED THE SUVs AND THE
PRIVATE PLANES.
THE REST OF US SHOULD BE
STANDING OUTSIDE WAITING FOR A
BUS EVERY 40 MINUTES ON A COLD
WINTER'S MORNING AND INSTEAD OF
USING A WASHER AND DRYER, WE
SHOULD BE BEATING OUR CLOTHES
DOWN BY THE RIVER ON THE ROCKS.
IT IS THE MOST EXPLICITDO
EXPRESSION OF THE NEW CLASS
POLITICS THAT MODERN-DAY
LIBERALISM IS IMPOSING ON US.
>> Tucker: IT IS FASCINATING.x
THAT IS WHY HE HAS HIKED THE
TOLLS TO COME INTO NEW YORK CITY
BECAUSE THE IDEA IS IF YOU DON'T
ALREADY LIVE IN MANHATTAN, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
IS SNOBBE
>> HE SAYS HE HAS TO GO TO HIS
GYM IN BROOKLYN.
TO COMMUNE WITH THE PEOPLE SO
HE'S NOT IN THE■ BIBLE.
HE IS DRIVEN THERE IN AN SUV BY
GUYS WITH REFLECTOR SHADES AND
TELEPHONE CORDS AND IF ANY
MEMBER OF THE MASSES TRIED TO
GET NEAR HIM DURING HIS PHOTO OP
AT THE GYM THEY WOULD BE TAKEN
OUT BY THE S.W.A.T. TEAM.
IT IS THIS PHONY POSER COMMUTING
WITH THE PEOPLE.
AND PHONY POSER
ENVIRONMENTALISM, TOO.
>> Tucker: THERE IS AN AWFUL
LOT OF THAT.
MARK STEYN, NOTHING PHONY ABOUT
MARK STEYN.
GREAT TO SEE YOU.
>> GREAT TO SEEWE YOU.
>> Tucker: WE ARE OUT OF TIME
BUT WE WILL BE BACK AND THAT IS
OURT PROMISE TO YOU.
TOMORROW NIGHT AT 8:00 P.M.
THE SHOW THAT IS THE