BACK BUT IT STILL FINISH LOWER.
THE OTHER MAJOR INDICES, THE S&P
AND NASDAQ WERE HIGHER.
WE HAVE SOME MAJOR EARNINGS OUT
THIS WEEK AND THIS WILL BE AN
EVENTFUL WEEK.
DON'T FORGET THE MARKETS, ALL
THREE MAJOR INDICES ABOUT 1.5
PERCENTAGE POINTS AWAY FROM
ALL-TIME HIGHS THANKS FOR
JOINING US.
NEIL WILL BE BACK TOMORROW.
CATCH ME TOMORROW ON "MAKING
MONEY" ON THE FOX BUSINESS
NETWORK.
"THE FIVE" STARTS RIGHT NOW.
♪ ♪
>> Greg: I AM GREG GUTFELD
WITH EMILY COMPAGNO,
JUAN WILLIAMS, JESSE WATTERS.
A FLOWERPOT AS HER HOT TUB.
NA PERINO.
"THE FIVE" ."X■■■■■■■■■TS KILLED
EANDREDS IN SRI LANKA ON
WHAT IS KEYHE HORROR
WAS THAT THE TARGETED COUNTRY
WAS AWARE OF THE THREAT AND THIS
NUGGET FROM "USA TODAY."
"THE COUNTRY'S PRIME MINISTER
AND HIS CABINET WERE UNAWARE OF
THE INTELLIGENCE UNTIL AFTER■,■■
DYSFUNCT■■■ POLITICAL
■### ■ IS
REALLY CODE FOR DEADLY
INCOMPETENCE AND TAKING YOUR EYE
OFF THE BALL.
IT IS SOMETHING TO REMEMBER, ASE
PHANTOMS OF THEIR OWN MAKING,
FEVER DREAMS OR
OCCLUSION, OBSTRUCTION,
IMPEACHMENT, HATE HOAXES, STORMY
AND AVENATTI IS THAT REAL EVIL
STILL STALKS THIS PLANET AND
TERROR IS LIQUID, ALWAYS SEEKING
THE PATH OF LEAK LEAST
RESISTANCE.
THE PATH IS OFTEN CARVED BY HER
OWN DISTRACTION SPARKED BY THOSE
WHO THINK POLITICS IS FAR MORE
IMPORTANT THAN OUR SAFETY WHICH
IS WHYERRORyyyyyy COMPETE WITH
THEUELLER REPORT EVEN ON
EASTER.
NOTHING MATTERS EXCINNING
THAT NEWS CYCLE.
IT HAPPEN FAR AWAY AND IN
AMERICA, IT'S PEACEFUL TIME
PEOPLE YOU DON'T KNOW MAKING
SURE IT'S STILL PEACEFUL UNTIL
ONE DAY WHEN TERROR STRIKES AS
AT HOME, AS IT HAS BEFORE.
WE CAN'T FORGET THAT AMERICA IS
TERROR TARGET NUMBER ONE AND
THAT OUR NUMBER ONE PRIORITY
ISN'T IMPEACHMENT BUT SECURITY,
OUR BORDERS, GRADE, LANDMARKS,
WATER, FOOD SUPPLY.
EVERYTHING IS UP FOR GRABS IN A
TIME WHERE TERROR HAS
SMARTPHONES TOO AND WHEN
SOMETH■■ STRIKES
WINNING A NEWS CYCLE LOOKS WHERE
THAN PETTY IT'S DOWNRIGHT
DANGEROUS.
EMILY, WE'VE TALKED ABOUT THIS
BEFORE.
AL QAEDA CAN COME AND GO.
I ISIS CAN DISAPPEAR BUT THERE
WILL ALWAYS BE AN IDEOLOGY AND
IT WILL ALWAYS GIVE BIRTH TO
SOMETHING NEW.
>> Emily: I AGREE.
WE'VE TALKED ABOUT IN THE
CONTEXT OF THEIREEDS TOB/ BE
SOME"/■/■/■/j■/■/■/j■/■/■/EVELS■
■/■/■/
I AGREHEN YOU HOARDINFORMATION E
LITICAL INFIGHTING THAT
WE ARE OEROUTRAJECTORY, NOT TO R
MONGER BUT WE ARE AS WELL.
IF THIS IS WHAT PEOPLE ARE
FOCUSED ON, IT
SHOULD BE
SECURITY FIRST.
I THINK YES, THE MESSAGING IS
IMPORTANT BECAUSE IT'S TRAVELING
AROUND THE WORLD.
>> Greg: DANA, THEY HAD A TWO
WEEK'S ADVANCED WARNING?
DID THEY NOT TAKE IT SERIOUSLY
OR WAS IT JUST SOMETHING THAT
JUST GOT LOST?
>> Dana: THEY WILL HAVE TO
FIND OUT BUT WHAT A WAY TO
FIGURE IT OUT, AFTERWARDS.
SECRETARY POMPEO WAS QUITE
GRACIOUS TODAY TO THE SRI
LANKANS, SAY THAT WE WILL HELP
AND PROVIDE THIS BUT WE'VE BEEN
HELPING AND WE HELP ALL THESE
COUNTRIES.
MAYBE THEY DON'T GET ENOUGH
FOREIGN AID AS THEY WOULD LIKE
BUT THEY HAVE TO DO SOMETHING
FOR US TOO.
THEY HAVE TO BE WILLING TO SHARE
THE INFORMATION WITH EACH OTHER
OR AT LEAST WITH US.
I GOT THE STATISTICS TODAY FROM
THE BRAIN ROOM, SINCE 2012,
23,177 CHRISTIANS HAVE BEEN
KILLED FOR FAITH-RELATED
REASONS.
23,000.
IT IS ABHORRENT, ACCEPTABLE, AND
IF WE ARE GOING TO PROVIDE AID
AND WERE GOING TO PROVIDE
INTELLIGENCE SERVICES, SHARING,
MILITARY GEAR, WHATEVER IT IS
THEY NEED, THE LEAST THEY CAN DO
IS PASS IT UP THE CHAIN THAT
THERE WAS GOING TO BE AN
ATTACKER COULD HAVE BEEN
PREVENTED.
>> Greg: JUAN, THERE WERE
EIGHT COORDINATED DETONATIONS.
THIS IS A GROUP WE'VE NEVER
HEARD OF BUT IT'S KIND OF THE
SAME THING, RIGHT?
IT MUTATES, CHANGES, EVOLVES,
GETS BETTER.
>> Juan: THIS IS THE ARGUMENT
THAT WE HAVE HERE BEFORE I START
THAT, LET ME SAY THE KIDS THAT
GRADER FROM A
SCHOOL IN D.C.
THREE OF THE FOUR CHILDREN OF A
DANISH BILLIONAIRE WHO IS THE
BIGGEST LANDOWNER IN BRITAIN.
I JUST CAN'T IMAGINE THE DEPTH
OF HIS SADNESS
■ PEOPLE WERE KILLED.
THIS WAS A WORLDWIDE EVENT IN
THAT SENSE.
IT TOUCHED US ALL.
I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT TO KEEP
IN MIND AND WE SEE IT IN THE
U.S., MORE SECURITY IN OUR
CHURCHES IN THE AFTERMATH OF
THIS, AND THERE WERE SOME
SUSPICIONS WENT BACK TO
NOTRE DAME IN PARIS.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
WHEN YOU HEAR PEOPLE SAY ISIS IS
DEFEATED, I WORRY ABOUT IT.
BECAUSE PEOPLE MIGHT THINK THEN
WE DON'T HAVE A THREAT BUT WE DO
HAVE A THREAT.
WE HAVE A THREAT, AS YOU
DESCRIBED, AS YOU SAID WATER
GOES WHEREVER THERE IS AN
OPENING.
WE SEE IS THIS IDEOLOGY SHIFTS
AND WE'VE NEVER HEARD OF THIS
GROUP.
ALL OF A SUDDEN THEY POP UP AND
THEY ARE BOMBING A CHURCH IN
SRI LANKA AND THEY ARE GOING
AFTER CHRISTIANS.
TO ME, IT'S A GENERATIONAL
FIGHT.
THE IDEOLOGY UNFORTUNATELY IS
NOT DEFEATED AND WE AS AMERICANS
CANNOT LOSE SIGHT OF THE FACT
THAT WE ARE IN AN ONGOING FIGHT.
WHEN THE PRESIDENT BOASTS FOR
WHATEVER REASON THAT ISIS IS
DEFEATED, DON'T BE FOOLED.
WE'VE GOT TO KEEP UP NOT ONLY
THE ATTENTION BUT THE FIGHT.
WITH REGARD TO THE INTELLIGENCE,
WE KNOW THERE'S SOME ARGUMENTS
ABOUT, DID WE KNOW WHAT WAS
COMING ON 9/11.
YOU CAN BLAME AND SAY THEY ARE
INCOMPETENT, THEY ARE NOT THE
U.S. GOVERNMENT, NOT U.S.
INTELLIGENCE, NOT ISRAELI
INTELLIGENCE.
THE FACT IS THE PEOPLE
RESPONSIBLE ARE THE TERRORISTS.
>> Dana: CAN I CLARIFY?
AFTER 9/11 IS WHEN WE TOOK DOWN
THE WALL BETWEEN INTELLIGENCE
AND LAW ENFORCEMENT.
THAT MADE A BIG DIFFERENCE.
THEN WE STEPPED UP EFFORTS ALL
AROUND THE WORLD TO MAKE SURE
THOSE GOVERNMENTS WHERE YOU KNEW
THAT THERE WERE HOT SPOTS WOULD
HAVE WHAT THEY NEEDED IN ORDER
TO SHARE THE INFORMATION AND
HAVE THE EQUIPMENT.
WE LEARNED A LESSON.
IF ARE GOING TO HELP THESE
COUNTRIES, THE LEAST THEY CAN
DO, THEY HAVE THE INFORMATION.
THEY DIDN'T PASS IT ON.
>> Juan: CORRECT.
I THINK WE'VE MADE CHANGES AND
WE HAVE ADAPTED POST-9/11 BUT I
JUST DON'T LIKE THE IDEA THAT WE
WOULD SAY IT'S THEIR FAILURE.
PEOPLE DID THAT TO US.
I DIDN'T LIKE IT.
I DIDN'T THINK WAS FAIR TO US OR
OUR GOVERNMENT.
I THINK THE TERRORISTS ARE THE
ONES WHO SHOULD BE HELD
RESPONSIBLE.
>> GSE, WE'VE SEEN
DIFFERENT RESPONSES, SOME ARE
ODD.
WOULD YOU CARE TO PICK THE ONES
THAT DISCUSSED YOU THE MOST?
>> Jesse: I HAVE
"THE WASHINGTON POST" HERE AND
IT'S JUST KIND OF DISGUSTING.
CHRISTIANITY UNDER ATTACK.
SRI LANKA CHURCH BOMBINGS STOKE
FAR RIGHT ANGER IN THE WEST.
IT'S A WHOLE ARTICLE, NOT ABOUT,
'S EDITORIALIZING SAYING
OH, CHRISTIANS ARE UPSET THAT
CHURCHES ARE BEING BOMBED.
THEY ARE MAKING CHRISTIANS AND
CONSERVATIVES OUT TO BE THE
VILLAINS FOR REACTING TO
TERRORIST ATTACKS.
LOOK AT SOME OF THE LEADING
DEMOCRATS, HOW THEY CHARACTERIZE
IT.
THEY DIDN'T USE CHRISTIANS.
THEY DIDN'T SAY CHURCHES.
HE ACTUALLY SAID EASTER
WORSHIPERS WERE UNDER ATTACK.
YOU DON'T CALL MUSLIMS
RAMADAN-WORSHIPERS.
YOU DON'T CALL JEWS
PASSOVER-WORSHIPERS.
IT'S A MADE-UP PHRASE.
WHY DID THEY MAKE UP PHRASES
LIKE THIS?
IT'S ONE OF THE REASONS PEOPLE
DON'T TRUST LIBERALS BECAUSE
THEY ARE NOT IN TOUCH WITH
REALITY.
THEY DO THIS BECAUSE THEY ARE
PANDERING TO MUSLIMS BECAUSE A
LOT OF LIBERALS FEEL THEY ARE SO
UPSET WITH HOW OTHER PEOPLE
THINK ABOUT THEM AND IF THEY ARE
THOUGHT UP TO BE INSENSITIVE, IT
DRIVES HIM CRAZY.
SECOND OF ALL, THEY THINK THEIR
OWN RHETORIC CAUSES ISLAMIC
EXTREMISM.
REMEMBER, BLAME AMERICA FIRST?
THEY THINK ISLAMAPHOBIA CAUSES
RADICAL ISLAM SO THEY DO
WHATEVER THEY CAN TO SANITIZE
IT.
BUZZFEED ACTUALLY CAME OUT, ONE
OF THEIR EDITORS, AND SAID
PRESIDENT TRUMP, IMAGINE HOW
OUTRAGED HE WOULD BE IF WHITES
WERE THE VICTIMS OF THE
SRI LANKA ATTACK.
I FOUND THAT COMPLETELY
DESPICABLE TO PLAY THE RACE CARD
AFTER A TERRORIST ATTACK.
IT'S WHAT THEY DID IN CATENA.
REMEMBER, BUSH?
HE WOULD'VE ACTED FASTER IF THEY
WERE WHITE VICTIMS IN LOUISIANA.
WHEN I STEP BACK AND THINK ABOUT
IT, CONSERVATIVES ARE PRETTY
COLOR-BLIND WHEN IT COMES TO
LIFE.
THEY DON'T TALK ABOUT THE
DIFFERENT RACES, BABIES AND THE
WARMS.
THEY WANT TO PROTECT ALL LIFE.
HAVE A LOT OF CONSERVATIVES IN
THE MEDIA WHO TALK ABOUT
STOPPING THE CARNAGE IN THE
SOUTH SIDE OF CHICAGO.
I THINK IT'S REALLY UNFAIR WHEN
THE MEDIA ALWAYS, NO MATTER WHO
DOES THAT, IF IT'S A WHITE
PERPETRATOR, MUSLIM PERPETRATOR,
HISPANIC PERPETRATOR, THEY JUST
TAKE THE VIOLENCE AND THEY TRIED
TO TURN IT AGAINST THE PRESIDENT
OR HIS SUPPORTERS AND I THINK
REALLY SHAMEFUL.
>> Greg: ALL RIGHT.
WELL, LET'S MOVE ON.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SMACKING DOWN
DEMOCRATS' IMPEACHMENT TALK
AFTER THE MUELLER REPORT.
HEAR FROM HIM NEXT.
Are we there yet?
You don't always use your
smartphone for directions.
Hey guys! Up there!
Or, to Laugh Out Loud.
You're in the middle.
But when it matters most,
you count on TracFone
to keep you connected,
for less.
♪
Our smartphone plan gives
you talk text and data
with Unlimited Carryover
starting at $15 a month,
no contract.
All with nationwide
4G LTE coverage.
Get top smartphones or
bring your own phone.
TracFone.
For Moments That Matter.
This is Loma Linda,
a place with one of the
highest life expectancies
Get top smartphones or
bring your own phone.
in the country.
You see so many people
walking around here
in their hundreds.
So how do you stay■■1■■■■
planning as early as possible.t
We all need to plan,
for 18 years or more,
i■■■■■■■0q■■qent.
I don't have a
whole lot saved up,
but I'm working on it now.
I will do whatever
I need to do.
Plan your financial
life with Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
There goes our first big order.
♪
44, 45, 46...
How many of these
did they order?
Ooh, that's hot.
♪
You know, we could sell these.
Nah.
♪
We don't bake.
Opportunity.
What we deliver by delivering.
Every day, NewDay helps veterans
buy a home with no down payment
■■■7■7
and not one dollar out of pocket
for closing costs.
No down payment, No closing
costs.
HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN'T GET
HIGH SPEED INTERNET WHERE YOU
LIVE? WELL YOU CAN, WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITET WHEREVER YOUó
LIVE. HUGHESNET GEN 5 IS FAST.
YOU'LL GET 25MBPS, PLUS BUILT-IN
WI-FI, AND THERE'S NO HARD DATA
LIMITS. SO, WHEREVER YOU LIVE,
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
EVERYTHING YOU LOVE ONLINE.
CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, STAY
INFORMED, WATCH THE LATEST
VIDEOS, AND HELP YOUR KIDS GET■
AHEA■■■■
AMERICA'S NUMBER ONE CHOICE FOR
SATELLITE INTERNET. ACT NOW TO
SAVE BIG WITH OUR LIMITED TIME
OFFER. GET FREE STANDARD
INSTALLATION BY CALLING RIGHT
NOW. SO, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING
FOR? GET HUGHESNET GEN5. TO
ORDER, CALL THE NUMBER ON YOUR
SCREEN. BE SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR
HOME PHONE SERVICE, TOO. CALL
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN
TODAY.
>> Juan: AT THIS MOMENT,
DEMOCRATS CONVENING A CONFERENCE
CALL TO FIGURE WHAT THEIR NEXT
MOVE WILL BE POSTMEAL REPORT.
SOME SAY IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS
COULD BE COMING AGAINST
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> IT IS CERTAINLY THE CASE THAT
IMPEACHMENT WOULD BE
UNSUCCESSFUL IF THE REPUBLICAN
PARTY CONTINUES TO PLACE PARTY
ABOVE COUNTRY.
>> YOU CAN SEE THAT THERE'S
ENOUGH INFORMATION THEY ARE NOT
ONLY ON OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE
BUT ALSO ON COLLUSION OR
CONSPIRACY, WHATEVER YOU WANT TO
CALL IT, T M FORWARD WITH
IMPEACHMENT.
>> I'VE CALLED ON THE HOUSE TO
INITIATE IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDING
PROCEEDINGS.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Juan: PRESIDENT TRUMP
MOCKING THE MOVE ON TWITTER.
HE SAYS:
"ONLY HIGH CRIMES AND
MISDEMEANORS CAN LEAD TO
IMPEACHMENT.
THERE WERE NO CRIMES BY ME
NO COLLUSION, NO OBSTRUCTION,
SO YOU CAN'T IMPEACH.
IT WAS THE DEMOCRATS THAT
COMMITTED THE CRIMES, NOT YOUR
REPUBLICAN PRESIDENT!
TABLES ARE FINALLY TURNING
ON THE WITCH HUNT!"
TRUMP ALSO DISMISSING THE
MUELLER REPORT AND IMPEACHMENT
THREATS EARLIER.
>> ARE YOU WORT YOUR
STAFF...
>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT, MR. PRESIDENT  ?
>> Juan: ALL RIGHT, DANA,
LET'S GO TO THE REALITY HERE,
WHAT ARE THE ODDS THAT THIS
CONFERENCE CALL, NANCY PELOSI IS
HOLDING.
>> Dana: IT'S HAPPENING RIGHT
NOW.
THE MOST PUBLICIZED CONFERENCE
CALL.
YOU CAN BET THERE'S 20 REPORTERS
ON THE CALL.
>> Juan: ONE ARGUMENT IS ABOUT
ACCOUNTABILITY.
SAYING THAT CONGRESS HAS A
RESPONSIBILITY TO HOLD THE
PRESIDENT ACCOUNTABLE.
THE OTHER ARGUMENT IS THAT IT'S
ONLY 18 MONTHS UNTIL THE NEXT
ELECTION AND THERE'S A DANGER
THAT YOU JUST ENERGIZED TRUMP'S
BASE BECAUSE HE WILL SAVE THE
DEMOCRATS ARE TRYING TO GET ME
OUT.
>> Dana: I THINK THE DEMOCRATS
BY THEIR OWN ADMISSION HAVE BEEN
DIVIDING INTO HOSTILE CAMPS.
OR AS PRESIDENT OBAMA REMINDERS,
CIRCULAR FIRING SQUAD IS WHEN
YOU TURN YOUR GUNS ON EACH
OTHER.
ON ONE SIDE YOU HAVE THE
CAUTIOUS OLD GUARD, THE
ESTABLISHMENT, THINK WE REMEMBER
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE REPUBLICANS
WHEN THEY DID IT TO CLINTON.
THAT THE REPUBLICANS HAVE EGG ON
THEIR FACE AND YOU HAVE THE
FORMER SPEAKER NEWT GINGRICH
SAYING THAT LOOKING BACK ON A
THAT MIGHT'VE NOT OF BEEN THE
BEST THING TO PURSUE.
THEN YOU HAVE THE FIREBRANDS
SAYING YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND, WE
WANT THIS.
THERE WAS A SURVEY, THEY PULLED
DEMOCRATS.
51% OF THOSE WHO ARE VERY
LIBERALS THAT WE WANT
IMPEACHMENT.
31 PER SAY WORTH THE DEMOCRATS
TIME TO PURSUE.
I THINK WHAT COULD HAPPEN IS
THAT YOU WILL GET HEARINGS AND
YOU WILL HAVE ONGOING THINGS IN
THE WALK UP TO THE LINE OF
IMPEACHMENT.
IT WILL BE HARASSMENT,
CONSIDERED HARASSMENT FROM THE
PRESIDENT'S PERSPECTIVE BUT THEY
WON'T QUITE ACTUALLY GO TO
IMPEACHMENT BECAUSE THEY KNOW
THAT IT WON'T PASS IN THE
CENTAGE.
THE OTHER THING I WOULD POINT
OUT, IN THE COMMERCIAL BREAK WE
SAW THAT THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE HAS SUBPOENAED DONALD
McGAHN, THE PRESIDENT'S FORMER
LAWYER.
HE WAS AT THE QUESTION OF THE
OBSTRUCTION PIECE.
>> Juan: JESSE, MUELLER IS
GOING TO HAVE TO TESTIFY AT SOME
POINT AND OF COURSE, AS DANA
POINTED OUT, YOUR -- SEVERAL
CONGRESSIONAL COMMITTEES
LAUNCHING THEIR OWN
INVESTIGATIONS.
IS IMPEACHMENT REDUNDANT?
>> Juan: I DON'T KNOW, JUAN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU JUST CRASHED
SURVEYMONKEY THAT.
>> Dana: WE DON'T PUT THEM
ONLINE.
>> Jesse: JUAN, DON'T CITE
LAURENCE TRIBE.
HE WAS OUT THERE FOR TWO YEARS
SAYING THAT THERE WAS COLLUSION.
HE PROBABLY GOT IT MORE WRONG
THAN ANYONE ELSE BESIDES ADAM
SCHIFF.
MAXINE WATERS, NO RELATION, THAT
MIGHT'VE BEEN ONE OF THE DUMBEST
THING SHE'S EVER SAID.
CAN YOU BELIEVE WHAT SHE JUST
SAID?
LET'S IMPEACH TRUMP FOR
COLLUSION.
DID SHE NOT READ THE MUELLER
REPORT?
THERE'S NO COLLUSION AND SHE
WANTS TO IMPEACH FOR COLLUSION.
JUAN!
HOW COULD YOU NOT NOTICE THAT?
IT'S THE DUMBEST THING SHE'S
EVER SAID.
>> Juan: I WILL LET YOU ARGUE
IT.
>> Jesse: PRESIDENT TRUMP
SURVIVED THE COUP AND THE
DEMOCRATS ARE FREAKING OUT
BECAUSE THEY THOUGHT THE MUELLER
REPORT WAS GOING TO DELIVER THE
GOODS AND IT DIDN'T.
HE HAS A FAT WAR CHEST, HOT
ECONOMY AND DEMOCRATS HAVE
DOZENS OF PEOPLE RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT AND THEY ARE ALL
CRAZY.
THEY KNOW THEY CAN'T WIN AT THE
BALLOT BOX SO THEY HAVE TO
IMPEACH ANOTHER MEDIA WANTS THEM
TO IMPEACH BECAUSE THEY FEEL
LIKE THEY HAVE TO JUSTIFY THE
HOAX THEY PERPETRATED FOR TWO
YEARS.
>> Juan: THE MEDIA WANTS IT?
>> Jesse: YEAH, THEY'VE BEEN
BEGGING FOR IT.
>> Juan: NANCY PELOSI HAS BEEN
VERY CLEAR THAT GIVEN THE SENATE
IS IN REPUBLICANS HANDS AND
THERE'S BEEN NO REAL DEPARTURE
OF REPUBLICANS FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP, SHE DOESN'T SEE
THE BENEFIT OF IMPEACHMENT.
THAT'S FROM NOT ONLY
NANCY PELOSI BUT HOUSE
LEADERSHIP AND WITH THE
EXCEPTION OF ELIZABETH WARREN,
ALL OF THE DEMOCRATS RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT.
>> Emily: PELOSI AND SOME OF
THEM HAVE BEEN CLEARED IN THAT
REGARD BUT PLENTY HAVE NOT AND
ARE FURTHERING THE IMPEACHMENT
FLAG ON THE LEFT.
TWO THINGS STRIKE ME.
WHEN ADAM SCHIFF SAYS IS IT IN
THE BEST INTEREST OF THE COUNTRY
TO PURSUE IMPEACHMENT?
MAYBE IT'S YES.
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
THE COLOSSAL EFFORT BEING
UNDERTAKEN BY THE HOUSE IN TERMS
OF THE COLLABORATION, THE
FINANCE COMMITTEE, INTELLIGENCE,
WAYS AND MEANS, 100-PLUS
SUBPOENAS, MOST OF THEM REQUIRE
VOTES ON THE COMMITTEES TO DO
SO.
THEY ARE SUBPOENAING THE U.S.
TREASURY DEPARTMENT,
DEUTSCHE BANK.
WHAT ARE THEY NOT DOING?
THEY ARE NOT LEGISLATING.
ALL OF THAT EFFORT IS TAKEN AWAY
FROM WHAT WE ELECTED THEM TO DO
AND WHEN WE TALK ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT, IT'S NOT JUST THE
EXPECTED $2 MILLION BUT THOSE
MAN-HOURS THAT WILL DETRACT FROM
WHAT I WOULD LOVE TO SEE JUST
HOW ABOUT WORKING ON BUILDING
BRIDGES RATHER THAN CONTINUING
TO BURN THEM.
>> Dana: INFRASTRUCTURE WEEK.
>> Jesse: IS OUT THIS WEEK OR
LAST WEEK?
>> Dana: EVERY WEEK.
>> Emily: THE SECOND POINT IS
IT'S INTERESTING PRESIDENT TRUMP
WENT TO THE COURTS TO BLOCK THE
SUBPOENA OF THE ACCOUNTING FIRM
BECAUSE IT UNDERMINES THE POWER
OF THE LEGISLATIVE BRANCH.
SAYING THAT THE COURT ORDER
MATTERS MORE.
I WILL GET DOWN THE RABBIT HOLE
OF WHAT HAPPENED WITH ERIC
HOLDER BUT WE SAW WHAT HAPPENED
WITH THE CONTEMPT ISSUES.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
ARREST HIM AND PROSECUTE HIM?
THE DOJ WOULD DO SO.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE --
>> Juan: LET IT ALL OUT.
WE WANT GREG TO TALK.
EVERYTHING SHE SAID BUT AT HALF
SPEED.
IT WENT FLYING OVER MY HEAD.
I SWEAR TO GOD.
DO KNOW I'M TIRED OF?
I AM TIRED OF THE COLLUSION
DRAMA QUEENS.
THESE ARE THE PEOPLE THAT ARE
ALWAYS TWEETING, LIKE I AM
SICKENED.
I'M LITERALLY SHAKING.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
PEOPLE LITERALLY SHAKING, WHEN
YOU'RE MUGGED OR YOU HEAR
TERRIBLE NEWS.
THEY ARE NOT LITERALLY SHAKING.
THE BEST ANALOGY IS FROM GLENN
REYNOLDS IN USA TODAY.
HE COMPARES THE LAST HOLDOUTS OF
COLLUSION TO A DOOMSDAY CULT.
DO YOU KNOW, THEY SET THE
APOCALYPSE DATE AND THEY GET IT
WRONG SO THEY MOVE IT.
IT'S A BRILLIANT ANALOGY AND I'M
STEALING IT FROM HIM.
WE ARE SEEING THE ARBITRARY
NATION OF THE WEAPONS BEING USED
TO GET RID OF TRUMP.
BECAUSE THEY DIDN'T GET
COLLUSION, THEY ARE MOVING TO
OBSTRUCTION.
IT REALLY DOESN'T MATTER.
TO YOUR POINT, IT REALLY IS A
COOL, A SLOW-MOTION COUP.
THEY ARE UNDOING THE WILL OF THE
PEOPLE.
JUST WIN, BABY, AS AL DAVIS
WOULD SAY.
JUST WIN AND YOU DON'T HAVE TO
UNDO THE WILL OF THE PEOPLE.
IF YOU DO THAT, YOU'RE GOING TO
HAVE ANGRY PEOPLE WHO ARE GOING
TO COME AFTER YOU.
I'M NOT SAYING IT'S GOING TO BE
VIOLENT.
I'M YOU'RE SAYING PEOPLE KNOW
WHEN YOU'RE STEALING FROM THEM
AND THIS WOULD BE A STOLEN
ELECTION.
YOU'VE GOT PLENTY OF TIME TO
WIN, BABY.
>> Juan: ONE LESS THING FOR
ALL OF YOU.
WHEN BILL CLINTON WAS IMPEACHED,
REPUBLICAN SAID YEAH, HE LIED.
HE'S A LIAR.
HE IS DISHONEST.
HE WAS ORDERING PEOPLE TO DO
THINGS THAT ARE WRONG.
IF YOU APPLY THE SAME STANDARD.
>> Greg: WE HAVE EVOLVED SINCE
THEN.
I HAVE EVOLVED.
>> J ALL RIGHT.
MSNBC UNDER FIRE FOR AMBUSHING
ROBERT MUELLER OUTSIDE HIS
CHURCH ON EASTER SUNDAY.
THAT VIDEO IS NEXT RIGHT HERE ON
"THE FIVE" FOR YOU TO SEE■
■■■ñ■■
There was a moment, my son I
believe was about four,
where he actually asked me
"Mommy what's wrong
with your teeth?"
If I would've known that I was
gonna be 50 tiier...
I would've gone into Aspen
Dental much sooner.
It was a very life changing
experience...
and it felt like I was me again.
That's when I realized I hadn't
been for three years.
At Aspen Dental we're
all about yes.
Like yes to flexible hours
and payment options.
Yes to free exam and x-rays
for new patients
without insurance.
And yes whenever you're
ready to get started,
we are too.
Call now at 1-800-AspenDental.
I switched to Liberty Mutual,
■■
because they let me
customize my insurance.
And as a fitness junkie,
I customize everything,
like my bike, and my calves.
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay
for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
Back then, we checked our
smartphones
zero times a day.
Times change. Eyes haven't.
hy there's Ocuvite.
Screen light...
Sunlight...
Longer hours...
Eyes today are stressed!
But Ocuvite has vital
nutrients
to help protect them.
Ocuvite.
Eye nutrition for today.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Jesse: WANT TO KNOW HOW THE
MAINSTREAM MEDIA SPENT
EASTER SUNDAY?
CHECK OUT THIS DESPICABLE VIDEO
OF AND MSNBC REPORTER AMBUSHING
ROBERT MILLER.
>> WILL YOU TESTIFY BEFORECONGR?
>> NO COMMENTS.
>> IF HE WERE ANYONE BUT THE
PRESIDENT, WOULD MR. TRUMP BE
INDICTED?
NOW THAT YOU'VE FINISHED.
>> SIR, WHY DIDN'T YOU MAKE OUT
RECOMMENDATION TO COMMERCE ONE
HE ?
>> TO THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
ACCURATELY CHARACTERIZE YOUR
POSITIONS ON CONSPIRACY AND
OBSTRUCTION?
>> I THINK IT'S ACCURATE TO
CHARACTERIZE DIRECTOR MUELLER AS
BEING TIGHT-LIPPED IN RESPONSE
TO MY QUESTIONS.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Jesse: EVEN I, WOULD NOT
AMBUSH SOMEONE COMING OUT OF
CHURCH ON EASTER SUNDAY.
>> Greg: ARE YOU SURE?
>> Jesse: WE DIDN'T HAVE A LOT
OF RULES WITH THOSE AMBUSHES.
ONE RULE WAS YOU DON'T EVER
ANYBODY ON A■IGIOUS
HOLIDAY.
Greg: THAT IS BIG
ATHEISTS DON'T HAVE ANY
PROTECTION.
>> Greg: THAT'S NOT FAIR.
SO I DON'T GO TO CHURCH.
THAT'S JUST WRONG.
>> Jesse: YOU'RE GOING TO GET
IT, GREG.
>> Juan: IT'S A PUBLIC
SIDEWALK.
HE'S NOT IHURCH.
HE CAN ASK THE GUY.S.
IT IS ONE ANSWER.
>> Jesse: I AGREE.
LISTEN, I'VE GOT PEOPLE COMING
OUT OF AA MEETINGS.
>> Greg: THAT'S TERRIBLE!>> JesR
CHILDREN GOT PEOPLE ON
PRIVATE PROPERTY.
>> Greg: YOU ARE WORSE THAN
THIS REPORTER.
>> Jesse: I HAVE NEVER PULLED
THE TRIGGER ON SOMETHING LIKE
THIS ON EASTER LEAVING CHURCH.
>> Greg: BUT YOU GOT THEM
OUTSIDE OF AA?
>> Jesse: I WAS RUTHLESS, I'M
NOT GOING TO LIE.
>> Dana: YOU DON'T WORK
WEEKENDS.
>> Greg: THAT'S TRUE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Dana: CAN I SAY --
>> Greg: I LOVE THAT THEY GAVE
YOU THIS SEGMENT.
>> Juan: JUST BROKE IT DOWN.
WE NEED YOU TO DEFEND THE GUY.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> Dana: THIS IS ONE OF THE
REASONS I DIDN'T MAKE IT IN
LOCAL NEWS.
BECAUSE I WAS ASKED, THERE WAS A
MURDER TRIAL AND I WAS SENT AS
YOUNG DAILY REPORTER A■2 w=
TO GO TO THE COURTHOUSE AND I
WAS SUPPOSED TO THE WOMAN
WHOSE CHILD HAD BEEN KILLED
RIGHT BEFORE THE TRIAL WAS
SUPPOSED TO START, I WAS
OSED TO GET UP TO HER AND
THEY SAID DON'T COME BACK WITH
OUT AN INTERVIEW.
I CIRCLED THREE TIMES AND I SAID
I'M NOT DOING THAT.
I WANT HOME AND I CALLED MY DAD
AND I SAID I THINK I JUST GOT A
DEGREE IN SUMMING I CAN'T DO.
ANYWAY, HERE I AM.
IT'S EASY TO BE HERE IN THE
I WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
IT.
>> Greg: THERE IS A POINT TO
THAT, AND WHAT YOU WERE SAYING,.
WHAT WE DO, WE DON'T EVER HAVE
TO BE FACED WITH THIS SORT OF
QUESTION EVERY DAY.
I THINK YOU GET INTO A MIND-SET
WHERE YOU ACTUALLY DON'T SEE
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YOU'RE JUST GOING OUT THERE.
HAVING SAID THAT, I WOULD SAY
THE MEDIA IS A RELIGION IN NEED
OF A REFORMATION.
SOCIAL MEDIAS LIKE THE GUTENBERG
PRESS.
AN UNTENABLE SITUATION FOR
EVERYBODY.
WE NOW KNOW WHAT'S FAKE AND
WHAT'S REAL.
IT'S SO EASY TO CALL EVERYTHING
OUT, THAT I THINK THE MEDIA HAS
NO RESPECT ANYMORE.
>> Jesse: I THINK THE REASON
WHY WHY THEY DID THIS, MSNBC
WANTED TO HUMILIATE ROBERT
MILLER BIGOTED RACHEL MADDOW WAS
HUMILIATED HERSELF.
>> Juan: OH, STOP.
YOU KNOW IT'S FUNNY TO ME, YOU
USED TO SAY YOU LIBERALS, YOU
MADE ROBERT MUELLER YOUR HERO.
NOW AFTER THE MUELLER REPORT,
AFTER YOU SPIN, YOU SAY MUELLER
IS THE HERO.
MSNBC IS ATTACKING ROBERT
MUELLER.
>> Jesse: I DON'T THINK THEY
ATTACKED HIM.
THEY JUST NAILED HIM ON THE
STREET.
>> Juan: PEOPLE WHO HAVEN'T
READ THE MUELLER REPORT ENGAGING
IN WILLFUL IGNORANCE IN ORDER TO
MAKE MUELLER THEIR HERO.
THAT'S WHAT'S GOING ON.
GIVEN WHAT YOU'VE DONE IN YOUR
PROFESSIONAL CAREER, WHY ARE YOU
FENDING OUT REPORTER DURING HIS
DRIVE ON PUBLIC STREETS?
>> Jesse: I ALREADY TOLD YOU
WE HAVE LIKE THREE RULES.
DO YOU WANT TO HEAR THEIR WAR
REST?
NO WEDDINGS, NO FUNERALS.
NO RELIGIOUS HOLIDAYS.
THAT'S IT.
I DID EVERYTHING ELSE.
>> Juan: JESSE.
>> Emily: MUELLER WAS NOT SOME
HOLLYWOOD CELEBRITY WHERE HE
EMERGES.
HE WAS COMING OUT OF EASTER
SERVICE.
HE ALREADY -- WE KNOW WHAT HE
THOUGHT.
IT WAS IN THE REPORT.
THE FACT THAT THEY WERE
CELEBRATING THE QUESTIONS
AFTERWARDS ON MSNBC, LIKE YES,
THOSE ARE EXACTLY THE QUESTIONS
THE PUBLIC WANTED TO KNOW BUT IT
DOESN'T MATTER BECAUSE YOU
DIDN'T GET ANY ANSWERS.
THERE WAS NO COMMENTS.
YOU KNOW YOU WHEN YOU'RE COMING
OFF THE HEELS OF SOMETHING LIKE
PEACEFUL LIKE YOGA OR CHURCHn■n.
I FEEL LIKE, WAY TO RUIN IT.
>> Dana: I HAD A FACIAL ON
SATURDAY AND I GET THE CAR AND
PETER ASKED ME 20 QUESTIONS
ABOUT AM I TAKING THE CAR AND I
WAS GETTING FLUSTERED.
I SAID I JUST CAME FROM A FACIAL
WHERE I WAS RELAXED AND NOW
YOU'RE ASKING ME 20 QUESTIONS.
>> Greg: THE THING THAT WE ARE
OVERLOOKING IS THAT BY GOING
AFTER MSNBC, WE ARE NOT GOING
AFTER BRIAN STELTER.
WHAT?
>> TRUMP AND HIS ALLIES ARE
TELLING BIG LIES.
RIGHT NOW THE MOST POPULAR ONE
IS NO OBSTRUCTION.
THERE IS NO CONSPIRACY FOUND IN
THE MUELLER REPORT, BUT THERE IS
NO INTEGRITY EITHER.
SO WHAT'S THE ROLE OF THE PRESS
IN THIS BROKEN ENVIRONMENT?
IN PART, OUR ROLE IS TO KEEP
COLLECTING FACTS, ALL OF THE
FACTS SO CITIZENS CAN MAKE UP
THEIR OWN MINDS.
I THINK IT'S ALSO OUR ROLES WITH
AN UPPER AND MORALITY.ESPECIALL.
>> Greg: [LAUGHS]
HE'S THE HAIRLESS HALL MONITOR.
HE JUST APPOINTED HIMSELF THE
ARBITER OF MORALITY AFTER LAYING
THE RED CARPET OUT FOR AVENATTI,
THE MOST AMORAL VERMIN SINCE THE
INVENTION OF THE COCKROACH.
HE EMBRACED AVENATTI BECAUSE HE
DID STELTER'S OWN BIDDING.
YOU CAN'T SIT ON YOUR SOAPBOX
BECAUSE IT MIGHT BREAK.
YOU CAN'T START LECTURING US
UNTIL YOU COME CLEAN ABOUT THE
MISTAKES YOU MADE.
>> Jesse: ELIZABETH WARREN
UNVEILING AN AMBITIOUS BIG
GOVERNMENT PLAN TO ELIMINATE
STUDENT DEBT.
THAT'S?á■■?á■■á?á?á■?á■■■á■á?■á;
Billions of mouths.
Billions of problems.
Morning breath? Garlic breath?
Stinky breath?
There's a TheraBreath for you.
TheraBreath Fresh Breath
Oral Rinse
instantly fights all types
of bad breath
and works for 24 hours.
So you can...
Breathe easy.
there's TheraBreath
at Walmart.
I don't keep track of regrets.
I never count the wrinkles.
And I don't add up the years.
But what I do count on...
is staying happy and healthy.
So, I add protein,
vitamins and minerals to my diet
BOOST®.
Delicious BOOST®
High Protein Nutritional Drink
has 20 grams of protein,
along with 26 essential
vitamins and minerals
your body needs.
All with guaranteed great taste.
The upside-
I'm just getting started.
BOOST® High Protein.
Be Up For Life™.
Look for savings on BOOST®
in your Sunday paper.
NewDay's Operation Home lets
veterans buy a home
with no down payment and
no closing costs.
Now there's no reason to rent
when you can buy.
,rjEVr■÷)wUdX<IX
H0b,
We humans are
strange creatures.
Other species avoid pain
And struggle.
We actually... seek it out.
Other species do
difficult things
Because they have to.■
We do difficult things.
Because we like to.
We think it's... fun.
Introducing the all-new
2019 Ford Ranger
Built for the strangest
of all creatures.
♪♪
Every day,
So, every day,
♪♪
The United States
Postal Service makes
more e-commerce
deliveries to homes
than anyone else
in t■/■/.
♪♪
Because the future only
happens with people
who really know how
to deliver it.
My experience with USAA
has been excellent.
They really appreciate
the military family
and it really shows.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
was funny because
It wwhen we would callngs and
another insurance company,
■÷sa“Oh we can't beat USAA”
It wwhen we would callngs and
We're the Webber family.
We're the Tenney's
We're the Hayles,
and we're USAA members for life.
♪
Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
♪ ♪
>> Dana: ELIZABETHREN
PROPOSING PERHAPS HER BIGGEST
POLICY IDEA YET.
SHE WANTS TO WIPE OUT STUDENT
LO■ÑÑ■■ÑÑz■Ñ■e■■e4 FOR 42 MILLIN
AMERICANS.
SHE EXPLAINS HOW HER PLAN WOULD
WORK.
>> ANYONE WHO'S GOT AN
OUTSTANDING STUDENT LONE DEBT
CAN HAVE UP TO $50,000 WORTH OF
STUDENT LONE DEBT CANCELED OUT
SO LONG AS THEIR INCOME IS UNDER
$100,000 AND IT KIND OF STEPPED
IN UP TO, THERE'S NO HELP FOR
ANYONE WHOSE FAMILY INCOME IS
ABOVE 250,000.
THAT'S IT.
>> Dana: HOW WOULD HER OVER
$1 TRILLION PROPOSAL BE PAID
FOR?
A WEALTH TAX ON MILLIONAIRES AND
BILLIONAIRES.
I LIKE TALK ABOUT POLICY STUFF.
SHE IS FLOODING THE ZONE WITH
POLICY PROPOSALS.
EVERY DAY.
YOU CAN'T CATCH UP WITH HER
BECAUSE SHE'S THROWING THINGS
OUT THERE.
IN A GRANITE STATE POLL TODAY,
SHE'S AT 5%.
SIX MONTHS AGO IN AUGUST, SHE
WAS AT 17%.
SHE HAS LOST THAT MUCH AROUND
DESPITE THE PROPOSALS.
>> Jesse: MAYOR PETE AND
SANDERS ARE SURGING IN THAT SAME
POLL.
I LIKE THE THOUGHT BEHIND IT.
I DON'T THINK REPUBLICANS SHOULD
SEE GROUND TO DEMOCRATS.
REPUBLICANS HAVE TO COME OUT
WITH THE IDEA THEMSELVES ABOUT
HOW TO TACKLE STUDENT LOANS DEBT
BECAUSE IT IS A HUGE PROBLEM.
HER IDEA IS UNCONSTITUTIONAL.
YOU CAN'T SEIZE WEALTH FROM
PEOPLE.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE AN INCOME TAX
AND I DON'T THINK SHE REALLY
CARES IF IT'S UNCONSTITUTIONAL
OR NOT.
IT'S MORE OF A P.R. GIMMICK.
INSTEAD OF THAT, WHY DON'T THEY
CREATE A FOUNDATION THAT LARGE
CORPORATIONS HEN AMERICANS AND
OTHER FOUNDATIONS CAN CONTRIBUTE
TO TAX-FREE.
STUDENTS WITH OVERWHELMING DEBT
CAN APPLY TO SEE IF THEY CAN
WIPE OUT SOME OF THAT DEBT FOR
THEM.
IT HAS TO BE DONE THROUGH THE
PRIVATE SECTOR BECAUSE THE
PRIVATE SECTOR IS THE ENTITY
THAT IS SEVERING THE MOST FROM
STUDENTS WITH OVERWHELMING DEBT
BECAUSE THEY ARE NOT MOVING OUT
OF THEIR PARENTS' BASEMENTS AND
SPENDING MONEY.
>> Dana: AND THEY ARE
DEFAULTING.
COULD THIS BE THE MOTHER OF ALL
MORAL HAZARDS?
IF THE ONLY ENTITIES ON THE HOOK
ARE THE TAXPAYERS, THE COST FOR
COLLEGE IS NOT GOING TO GO DOWN.
>> Greg: THIS IS THEFT.
THIS MONEY ISN'T DISAPPEARING.
IT'S BEING TAKEN FROM SOMEBODY.
WHAT ABOUT CARLOS, HOME LOANS,
HOW ABOUT MY LOAN TO THE PAWN
SHOP?
HOW IS THAT ANY DIFFERENT?
CREDIT CARD DEBT.
IT DOESN'T HURT THE PEOPLE THAT
YOU WANT TO HURT, COLLEGES.
THEY ALREADY MADE THE MONEY.
YOU WANT THE COLLEGES, WITH
THEIR BLOATED BUREAUCRACY AND
INFRASTRUCTURE, YOU WANT THEM TO
BE POKED.
LET'S FACE IT.
BECAUSE THE LOANS WERE SO EASY,
THAT'S WHAT INFLATED THE
INFRASTRUCTURE AND INFLATED THE
TUITION.
TRIPLED THE TUITION IN OVER TWO
DECADES BECAUSE THEY GOT THE
MONEY.
I AM FOR FREE COLLEGE.
I WANT COLLEGE TO BE FREE JUST
SO THE MASSIVE BUREAUCRACIES ARE
DESTROYING.
THERE'S A WAY TO DO THAT.
IF CORPORATIONS REJECT THE
VIRTUE SIGNALING OF ADVANCED
DEGREES AND EMBRACE ONLINE
ACADEMIA, ONLINE COLLEGES CAN DO
IT.
THAT COULD BE FREE.
MILITARY SERVICE, PRIORITY OVER
COLLEGE.
ALTERNATIVE EDUCATION, TRADE
SCHOOLS.
MAKE ELITE DIPLOMAS THAT COST SO
MUCH MONEY WORTHLESS.
THAT'S GREAT BECAUSE THE PROBLEM
IS THE LOANS ARE TOO EASY AND
SHE IS SO DESPERATE.
SHE IS LIKE A CHILD BANGING POTS
AND PANS IN THE KITCHEN WHERE
SHE CAN'T GET ENOUGH.
SHE WANTS NOISE AND IT'S NOT
WORKING.
>> Dana: THIS WASN'T DETAILED
IN THE PROPOSAL BUT IF YOUR DEBT
IS FORGIVEN, IT'S LIKE WINNING A
CAR ON A GAME SHOW.
YOU HAVE TO PAY TAXES ON IT.
LET'S SAY YOU GET $150,000
FORGIVEN, YOU STILL HAVE TO COME
UP WITH 25% OF THAT TO PAY THE
TAXES.
>> Emily: DO YOU REMEMBER THAT
SCENE IN "16 CANDLES."
SHE WAS LIKE BREAKFAST IS
SERVED.
IT'S A TOTAL OVERSIMPLIFICATION
AND MISSING THE POINT.
WHEN SHE TALKS ABOUT ERADICATING
TUITION, WHAT DO WE THINK THE
MAJORITY OF TUITION COVERS?
PENSIONS.
WE HAVE TALKED ABOUT THIS
BEFORE, THE ENTIRE PENSION
DEBACLE, SO SHE THINKS ANY TYPE
OF UNION WOULD GO FOR THIS
METHOD IT MAKES ANY FISCAL
ECONOMIC SENSE THAT TWO PLUS TWO
EQUALS FOUR, HE DOESN'T IN THIS
CASE.
IN CALIFORNIA, THIS GENERATION
IS LITERALLY PAYING FOR THE
GENUS DECISION OF 10 IN 20 YEARS
AGO TO ERADICATE EXTRA PAYMENTS
FOR THEIR PENSION.
IT IS SO MUCH MORE COMPLICATED
THAN SHE'S MAKING IT SEEM.
SHE SHOULD INCENTIVIZE
BUSINESSES TO HIRE STUDENTS TO
HAVE INTERNS, HIRE EMPLOYEES.
>> Dana: JUAN, DO YOU THINK
OTHER DEMOCRATS ARE GOING TO
COME FORWARD WITH SOME SORT OF
PLAN?
DOES IT HELP THE PEOPLE WHO
NEEDED THE MOST?
>> Juan: GREG WAS SAYING HE
WANTS TO HURT THE COLLEGES BUT I
THINK THE IDEA IS TO HELP
STUDENTS.
STUDENTS WHO ALREADY HAVE
ACCRUED SUBSTANTIAL DEBT AND ARE
OUT OF SCHOOL.
THEIR PLANS ARE KNOWN PLACE,
SOME PEOPLE TALKING ABOUT IT TO
HELP IN THE FUTURE, PEOPLE WOULD
INCUR FUTURE DEBT.
THERE ARE SO MANY PEOPLE RIGHT
NOW STRUGGLING WITH STUDENT
DEBT.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT THIS,
WHATEVER SHE SAID, I THINK IT'S
REASONABLE TO MY EARS, WHAT
STRIKES ME IS ORIGINAL PLAN FROM
THE REPUBLICANS.
THE REPUBLICANS AREN'T DEBATING
IT.
THEY ARE GIVING UP ON THE WHOLE
IDEA OF RUNNING UP CRAZY TAX
DEBTS AND DEFICITS.
TRUMP HAS NO PLAN OR LEASING THE
DEFICIT RISING EVERY DAY.
SHE WANTS TO USE THIS MONEY TO
HELP YOUNG PEOPLE WHO ARE TRYING
TO MOVE AHEAD.
BY THE WAY, GREG, THOSE ONLINE
SCHOOLS, A LOT OF FRAUD.
WE SAW IT RECENTLY, BY THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION, POINTING OUT
SECRETARY DeVOS AND OTHERS.
YOU'VE GOT TO LOOK AT WHAT'S
GOOD FOR YOUNG PEOPLE.
>> Greg: THERE'S A LOT OF
FRAUD IN ALL COLLEGES.
I THINK ONLINE IS THE WAY TO GO
HOME.
AND I HOPE THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS.
>> Dana: JUSSIE SMOLLETT'S
BROTHER MAKING A SHOCKING CLAIM
ABOUT THE TROUBLES AFTER.
DETAILS AHEAD.
Great tasting, heart-healthy
California Walnuts.
So simple, so good.
Get the recipes at walnuts.org.
At Carvana,
we have only one standard
when it comes to the quality
of our cars: The highest.
It's why only 1 in 10 cars
we look at
qualify to sell on our site.
If it's been
in a reported accident,
we won't sell it.
And at our
state-of-the-art facilities
our ASE certified mechanics
roll up their sleeves
■■■xE
Inspecting, dialing-in,
and fine tuning every single car
inside and out,
bringing all of it up
to our high standards.
By the time we're done,
our cars are
beyond "certified."
They're Carvana certified.
So whether you have it delivered
or pick it up,
we do it all
so you can rest easy.
You might take something
for your heart...
or joints.
But do you take something
for your brain.
With an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish,
Prevagen has been shown
in clinical trials
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
If your moderate to severe
ulcerative colitis
or Crohn's symptoms...
are holding you back...
and your
current treatment
hasn't worked
well enough...
it may be
time for a change.
Ask your doctor
about ENTYVIO®,
the only biologic
developed and approved
just for UC and Crohn's.
ENTYVIO® works at the
site of inflammation
in the GI tract,
and is clinically proven
to help many patients
achieve both symptom
relief and remission.
Infu serious
allergic reactions
can happen during
or after treatment.
ENTYVIO® may
increase risk of infection,
■can be serious.
PML, a rare, serious,
potentially fatal
brain infection
caused by a virus
may be possible.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection,
experience frequent
infections
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
prob?■?■ oc ENTYVIO®.
infections
If your UC or
Crohn's treatment
isn't working for you,
ask your gastroenterologist
about ENTYVIO®.
ENTYVIO®.
Relief and Remission
within reach.
>> Emily: JUSSIE SMOLLETT IS
STILL REFUSING TO ADMIT HE
STAGED A HATE CRIME ATTACK AND
FURTHER, CLAIMING THE DISGRACED
ACTOR IS REALLY ASSAULT■
VICTAS BSELY
ACCUSED BY POLICE OF MAKING IT
UP.
HIS BROTHER SAYING "JUSSIE A
STRONGER FOLLOWING AN ATTACK
LIKE■■Ñ■■ÑÑÑÑ■Ñ■■■■■ÑÑ■ A NORMAÑ
AMOUNT OF TRAUMA EVERYONE WOULD
SUFFER.
SOME OF MY SIBLINGS AS WELL AS
JUSSIE'S PARTNER AND CLOSEST
FRIENDS."
WHAT STRUCK ME ABOUT THIS IN
ADDITION TO THE LUDICROUS ASPECT
WAS THE FACT THAT IF THEY'RE
TRYING TO START A PAPER TRAIL OF
THERE BEING A PHYSICAL
MANIFESTATION OF DAMAGES IF THEY
ARE LAYING THE GROUNDWORK FOR A
LAWSUIT BY JUSSIE SMOLLETT
AGAINST THE CITY OF CHICAGO, I
JUST HOPE THEY ARE NOT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, GREG?
>> Greg: EVEN HAVE TO HAVE A
TREMENDOUS NUMBER OF PEOPLE
INVOLVED IN THIS FRAME UP, LIKE
10,000 PEOPLE.
AS SOMEONE WHO DOES EXPERIENCE
NIGHT TERRORS, I EXPERIENCE THEM
WITHOUT EVER PERPETRATING A
MASSIVE HOAX WHICH EMBARRASSES
YOUR FAMILY, YOUR COWORKERS,
PEOPLE WHO DEFENDED YOU.
I CAN SAY GO SCREW YOURSELF.
HE RAN UP HIS VICTIM DEBT CARD.
EVERYONE HAS A VICTIM DEBT CARD.
HE WANTS MORE.
HE WANTS TO GET EXTENSION
YOU'RE NOT■NY MORE FROM
ME.
BY THE WAY, NIGHT TERRORS, THEY
ARE BAD.
I HAVE HAD THEM.
>> Emily: WHAT'S THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A NIGHT
TERROR AND ARE NORMAL NIGHTMARE?
>> Greg: SLEEP PARALYSIS.
YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE AWAKE.
>> Jesse: I AM GOING TO SEE
YOUR "16 CANDLES" ANALOGY AND
RAISE YOU "WEDDING CRASHERS."
THE FREAKY SON TODD, MEMBER THE
WEIRDO?
IT DOESN'T MAKE PEOPLE FEEL BAD
FOR YOU.
IT MAKES PEOPLE LAUGH AT YOU.
NIGHT TERRORS IS WHEN YOU COME
HOME FROM IRAQ AND AFGHANISTAN.
>> Dana: THANK YOU.
>> Jesse: I'M NOT GOING TO
MAKE A REQUEST TO MAKE AN
ANALOGY.
SMOLLETT IS THE MEDIA.
THEY BOTH PERPETUATED A HOAX.
THEY BOTH GOT CAUGHT AND INSTEAD
OF BEING CONTRITE, THEY ARE
DOUBLING DOWN ON THE HOAX.
THEY NEED TO LAY LOW, STOP
HAVING THEIR TEAM RIGHT BEDS AND
WAIT UNTIL IT BLOWS OVER.
>> Emily: ISN'T THIS THE
BROTHER JUSSIE SMOLLETT
PRETENDED TO BE WHEN HE WAS
PULLED OVER?
>> Dana: THANK YOU, EXACTLY.
AND KIM FOXX, SHE'S THE ONE WHO
SAID IN THE TEXT MESSAGE THAT
WAS REVEALED LAST WEEK THAT HE
IS A LIAR.
SHE SAYS THAT HE LIED TO THE
COPS.
I WOULD SAY TO THE BROTHER, NEXT
TIME YOU THINK YOUR BROTHER IS
HAVING A NIGHT TERROR AND YOU
ARE WITNESSING IT, HE IS AN
ACTOR.
>> Emily: TOTALLY.
JUAN, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> Juan: IT'S NATURAL FOR HER
BROTHER TO STAND UP FOR ANOTHER
BROTHER.
IT'S HIS BROTHER AND HE FELT HE
SHOULD STAND UP AND SAY YOU KNOW
IT, GIVE MY BROTHER THE BENEFIT
OF THE DOUBT.
>> Emily: DO YOU THINK HE
BELIEVES THAT YOUR DO YOU THINK
HE'S JUST STANDING UP FOR HIM?
>> Juan: I DON'T KNOW BECAUSE
I'M NOT IN HIS HEAD BUT I THINK
JUSSIE SMOLLETT CONTINUES TO SAY
THAT IT HAPPENED AS HE SAYS.
OBVIOUSLY THE CHICAGO POLICE
DON'T FEEL THAT WAY.
EVEN CHARLES BARKLEY DOESN'T SEE
IT THAT WAY.
>> Dana: EVEN KIM FOXX.
>> Juan: I'M SAYING JUSSIE
SMOLLETT HASN'T CHANGED.
THE POLICE, PROSECUTION.
HE'S NOT FACING CHARGES.
AT SOME POINT YOU'VE GOT TO
THINK WHY IS THE SYSTEM, WHY IS
THE GOVERNMENT CONTINUING TO
PURSUE A MAN WHO REALLY HAS BEEN
CHARGED WITH NOTHING?
THEY HAVE THEIR INVESTIGATION,
NO CHARGES.
>> Greg: WAIT, ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT TRUMP?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Juan: THERE WAS A MISTAKE.
>> Emily: ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS.
"ONE MORE THING" IS UP NEXT.
Introducing... Smartdogs.
The first dogs trained to train
humans.
Stopping drivers from: Liking.
Selfie-ing.
And whatever this is.
Available to the public...
never.
Smartdogs are not the answer.
But GEICO has a simple tip.
Turn on "Do Not Disturb While
Driving" mode.
Brought to you by GEICO.
Excuse me a minute...
Hi Dad. No.
Don't try to get up.
Hi, I'm Julie, a
Right at Home caregiver.
And if I'd been caring
for Tom's dad,
I would have noticed
some dizziness that
could lead to balance issues.
That's because I'm trained to
report any changes in behavior,
no matter how small, so Tom
could have peace of mind.
We'll be right there.
We have to go.
Hey, Tom.
You should try Right at Home.
They're great for us.
The Right Care. Right at Home.
It's tough to quit
smoking cold turkey.
So CHANTIX can help
you quit “slow turkey.”
Along with support,
CHANTIX is proven
to help you quit.
With CHANTIX you can
keep smoking at first
and ease into quitting
so when the day arrives,
you'll be more ready to
kiss cigarettes goodbye.
When you try
to quit smoking,
with or
without CHANTIX,
you may have nicotine
withdrawal symptoms.
Stop CHANTIX and
get help right away
if you have changes in
behavior or thinking,
aggression, hostility,
depressed mood,
suicidal thoughts
or actions, seizures,
new or worse heart or
blood vessel problems,
sleepwalking, or
life-threatening allergic
and skin reactions.
Decrease alcohol use.
Use caution driving or
operating machinery.
Tell your doctor if you've
had mental health problems.
The most common
side effect is nausea.
Talk to your doctor
about CHANTIX.
The most common
side effect is nausea.
Since you're heading off to
school, I got you this Brita.
Dad... I just got a ZeroWater.
But we've always used Brita.
it's two stage-filter...
doesn't compare to ZeroWater's
5-stage.
This meter shows how much
stuff,
or dissolved solids, gets left
behind.
Our tap water is 220.
Brita? 110...
Seriously?
but ZeroWater-
Let me guess. Zero?
Yup, that's how I know it is
the purest-tasting water.
I need to find the
receipt for that.
Oh yeah, you do.
The Lexus ES.
Every curve, every
innovation, every feeling.
A product of mastery.
Lease the 2019 ES 350 for
$389 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing
at your Lexus Dealer.
NewDay USA's Operation Home
helps veterans
buy a home with no down payment
and not one dollar out of pocket
for closing costs.
And NewDay can say yes
when banks say no.
♪ ♪
>> Juan: THE EASTER BUNNY WAS
AT THE CENTER OF ATTENTION IN
ORLANDO LAST NIGHT, AND NOT
BECAUSE HE WAS THROWING
CHOCOLATES AT KIDS, HE WAS
THROWING KNUCKLES, TAKE A LOOK
AT THE VIDEO.
[LAUGHTER]
AT FIRST BUT SEEMED HOPPING TO
BREAK UP THE FIGHT, BUT THEN HE
GETS IN THE FIGHT, AND HE NEVER
GETS OUT OF COSTUME.
MY FAVORITE PART OF THIS VIDEO,
HIS SHADOWBOXING AT THE VERY
END.
THE EASTER BUNNY, YES, THE
EASTER BUNNY AND MUHAMMAD ALI, I
GUESS HE WAS JUST HOPPING MAD.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Jesse: SO EVERYBODY SENT ME
THIS VIDEO OVER THE WEEKEND, AN
8-YEAR-OLD GIRL DURING HER AOC
IMPRESSION.
WATCH THIS.
>> SOCIALISM IS SO AMAZING,
SOCIALISM ACTUALLY IS SHORT FOR
SOCIAL MEDIA, DID YOU KNOW THAT?
I AM ON SOCIAL MEDIA, SO I AM A
SOCIALIST, AND IT IS THREE OF
THE MOST SUCCESSFUL COUNTRIES IN
THE WORLD ARE SOCIALIST TOO,
FACEBOOK, AND TWITTER.
I HAVE A LOT OF FRIENDS FROM
FACEBOOK.
>> Jesse: HER NAME IS AVAMARTINT
IMPRESSION.
I THINK THAT I SHOULD HAVE HER
ON "WATTERS' WORLD" ."
>> Greg: I WOULD NOT BE
SURPRISED IF YOU HAVE HER
"WATTERS' WORLD."■n■kN, T■á■n■8.
OOK.Lá♪Lá■n■n■n■n■nLáLá ♪■n
♪♪ ANIMALS ARE GREAT ♪
♪ ANIMALS ARE GREAT ♪♪
DO WE NEED Ar■ LITTLE BREAK FROM
THE ANIMALS?
I LOVE THIS, SOMETIMES ANIMALS
CAN BE REAL JERKS.
TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT THE ELEPHANT
AIDE, CAME UP BEHIND HIS
ELEPHANT BUDDY AND SAID, LET ME■
HELP YOU, AND YOU CAN TELL, WE
WATCH THAT AGAIN, YOU CAN TELL
THAT IT WAS COMPLETELY
PREMEDITATED, PROBABLY SAID, I'M
TIRED OF YOUR CRAP, AND WHAT IF
THAT ELEPHANT■nLD NOT SWIM,HnHnT
THATJá■áLáLáLáLá■kLáLá ELELá■n■♪
♪ ANIMALS ARE GREAT ♪
♪ ANIMALS ARE GREAT ♪♪
>> Dana: I WILL RAISE YOUR
"PRETTY IN PINK" AND "WEDDING
CRUSHERS" AND DO "WHEN ARDEN MET
STELLA."
STELLA FOR THE FIRST TIME, AND
PUPPY.VERY EXCITED TO GET A
WE HAVE A PUPPY, AND ARDEN IS
TWO YEARS OLD.
>> Greg: THAT IS LIKE "THE
HARRY MET SALLY" DINING SCENE.
>> Dana: SHE CAN BE A THERAPY
DOG, THAT'S WHAT THE PLAN IS FOR
THE LITTLE ONE AS WELL.
CONGRATULATIONS, ARDEN.
>> Greg: YES, I GUESS SO.
ALL RIGHT, EMILY, IT'S UP TO YOU
TO FINISH THE SHOW AND A GOOD
WAY.
>> Emily: THIS WEEKEND IT WAS
EASTER AND I WANTED TO SHARE A
FEW PHOTOS OF MY FAMILY, SO HERE
ARE MY THREE NIECES, THAT IS
LITTLE LEONA DYING EGGS, AND
THAT IS LITTLE RILEY DYING EGGS
AS WELL, SO THIS IS THEM IN THE
GUARD, THAT IS LEONA WITH THE
LITTLE CHICKEN BASKET THAT I
THINK IS SO CUTE, BUNNY BASKET,
WHATEVER IT IS.
JOSEPHINE ON THE LEFT, VIOLET IN
THE MIDDLE, LEONA ON THE RIGHT.
>> Dana: IT WAS COLD?
>> Emily: THAT WAS IN SEATTLE,
THAT IS VIOLET WITH HER BASKET,
AND THEY WENT TO THE TULIP
FESTIVAL.
>> Greg: ARE THOSE THE TULIPS?
>> Emily: YES.
>> Greg: TAKE YOULD TO
WORK AND EARTH DAY TO BRING SOME
EARTH TO WORK DAY.
EVERYBODY BRING A PAIL OF DIRT
AND POUR IT ON YOUR BOSSES DESK.
DO IT TOMORROW.