♪ ♪
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
WATCHING "OUTNUMBERED OVERTIME""
I'M IN FOR HARRIS FAULKNER.■1■/.
>> Dana: YES, "THE DAILY
BRIEFING" STARTS NOW.
THREE BIG STORIES TO START
FINALLY, THE WAITING GAME IS
OVER.
UP NEW DETAILS ABOUT JOE BIDEN'S
MUCH-ANTICIPATED AND TALKED
ABOUT.
SYRIA       ZERO ONE, A NEW WAG
TO TERRORISTS.
■#■#■#■#■#■#■>ñ=■>ñ>ñ>ñ>ñ>ñ>ñ>ñN
PLAYING OUT DURING ORAL
ARGUMENTS.
SOME JUSTICES SEEM■>■■ SHOW
SUPPORT FOR INCLUDING EXISTS,
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION AND THE
2,020 CENSUS.
THIS IS GETTING A LOT OF
ATTENTION.
THERE ARE PROTESTERS THERE AND A
BIG ARGUMENT TODAY.
>> MOST OF THEM WALKED AWAY FOR
NOW BECAUSE I ARGUMENTS ARE OVER
BUT THEY WERE THERE EN MASSE
EARLIER THIS MORNING.
THIS COULD BE THE BIGGEST TEST
OF THE HIGH COURT'S NEW
CONSERVATIVE MAJORITY TO DATE.
PARTISAN LINES DEVELOP VERY
QUICKLY DURING ORAL ARGUMENTS
THIS MORNING, AND THAT THEY
PRESS THE LAWYERS FOR THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT TO EXPLAIN
WHY THE ARGUMENT WANTS TO
INCLUDE, ARE YOU AT A CITIZEN OF
THE UNITED STATES ON ITS 2020
CENSUS.
THE LIBERAL SCIENCES SAY IF THE
QUESTION IS INCLUDED AS MANY AS
6.5 MILLION PEOPLE MAY NOT
PARTICIPATE IN THE CENSUS.
CONSERVATIVE ASK IF IT WOULD
CAUSE AN INACCURATE CENSUS.
INCLUDING A PERSON'S AGE AND.
INDEED, THE QUESTION HAD BEEN ON
PREVIOUS CENSUSES FOR ALMOST 200
YEARS.
THE QUESTION WAS ASKED IN
CENSUSES FROM31950.9■9■9■9■Y%Y%■
■■AS IT DOE AMIDST THE■■
HEATED DEBATE, THEY ARE ADAMANT
IT NOT BE INCLUDED EVEN THE FACT
THAT IT IS ILLEGAL FOR THE
CENSUS BUREAU TO USE THAT
SURVEYS "FOR ANY INFORMATION
WHICH IDENTIFIES A PERSON OR A
BUSINESS.
>> WELL, YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE A
CONSPIRACY THEORIST TO BE
CONCERNED THAT IF THAT DATA IS
OUT THERE IT COULD POSE A RISK
TO YOU.
WE HAVE SEEN AN ADMINISTRATION
THAT IS PICKING PEOPLE UP IN
SENSITIVE PLACES LIKE COURT
HOUSES, SCHOOLS, GOING TO THE
DOCTOR'S OFFICE.
>> THE RAMIFICATIONS OF AND
UNDERCOUNT ARE HUGE AND OF THE
CENSUS WILL DETERMINE HOW MANY
ELECTORAL VOTE'S THE STATE HAS.
HOW MANY CONGRESSIONAL MEMBERS
OF THE STATE HAS AND HOW FEDERAL
RESOURCES ARE DEBATED OUT TO THE
STATES.
THE COURT WILL HAVE TO RULED BY
THE END OF IT SESSION THE
TRADITIONAL DEADLINE, THAT OF
PRINTING OFFICE WHICH
HAVE TO HAVE■÷■y■■■■ THEM MEET E
CENSUS WHICH GETS UNDERWAY.
>> THANKS FOR THAT REPORT.
LET'S BRING OUR OWN BRET BAIER,
ALWAYS GLAD TO HAVE YOU ON THE
SHOW.
SO THERE IS THE REPORT THAT DOUG
HAD AND THEN THERE'S ALSO THIS
FROM THE FORMER SOLICITOR
GENERAL.
HE WAS THERE, AND HE TWEETED
THIS.
JUST COMING OUT OF CENSUS
ARGUMENT SCOTUS.
INTERESTING THAT TRUMP SOLICITOR
GENERAL CRITICIZED SEVERAL
JUSTICES FOR THE VERY SAME THING
AS AG BARR CRITICIZED WITH A FEW
SELECT FACTS FROM THE RECORD AND
IGNORING THE REST.
MUST BE SOMETHING IN THE WATER.
SO AS THESE THINGS GO EVERYONE
TRIES TO REBUILD TEA LEAVES OF
WHAT THE JUSTICES MIGHT DO.
>> Bret: IT'S DANGEROUS TO DO
JUST BY ORAL ARGUMENTS.
SOMETIMES THE JUSTICES HAVE THE
WAY THAT THEY GO ABOUT IT BY
ASKING QUESTIONS THE OTHER WAY,
AND THEY MAY COME DOWN ON THE
ACTUAL CASE.
THAT ASIDE, THEY DID SEEM THAT
THE CONSERVATIVE LEADING
JUSTICES ON THE COURT ARE SIDING
WITH THE GOVERNMENT AND
EVERYTHING THEY ARE SAYING AND
ASKING AND IT LOOKS LIKE THEY
COULD SET UP TO A 5-4 RULING TO
ALLOW THE CENSUS QUESTION TO GO
FORWARD.
HIS CONTROVERSIAL, THERE'S ALL
KINDS OF PUSHBACK BUT THE BOTTOM
LINE ARGUMENT FROM THAT SIDE IS,
YOU NEED AN ACCURATE COUNT AND
THE VOTING RIGHTS ACT DEMANDS IT
ACCORDING TO THE PEOPLE WHO
SUPPORT THAT.
>> Dana: I READ A LOT OF THE
BACK AND FORTH ON THAT TODAY AND
FROM THE LEFT SIDE LOOKING AT
IT, THEY ARE MAKING VERY
TECHNICAL ARGUMENTS ABOUT THE
LAW AND THE SPECIFICS OF THE
ADMINISTRATIVE PROCEDURES ACT
AND WHAT THE SECRETARY OF
COMMERCE DID OR DID NOT DO.
THE QUESTION FOR VOTERS WILL BE,
WHY WOULD YOU NOT ASK THAT?
HE WAS ASKED UP UNTIL 1950.
>> Bret: AND THE OTHER
PUSHBACK IS THAT THEY WOULD BE
INTIMIDATING PEOPLE BY NOT
GETTING AS MANY RESPONDENTS, BUT
THEY DO WANT TO KNOW THE
CITIZENSHIP QUESTIONS.
SO THE BALANCE -- WHETHER YOU
INTIMIDATE PEOPLE OR DON'T GET
AS MANY WERE IT'S MORE AND
THEREBY BETTER FOR THE
GOVERNMENT.
>> Dana: THE OTHER THING THAT
WE FOUND OUT TODAY AS THERE IS
NO CONFIRMATION THAT JOE BIDEN
WILL BE ANNOUNCING HIS
PRESIDENTIAL RUN THIS THURSDAY,
AND THERE IS A MONMOUTH POLL
THAT JUST CAME OUT THAT SHOWS
THAT HE IS STILL ON TOP.
BUT STILL AT 27%.
I KNOW A LOT OF THAT IS NAME
I.D. BUT DO YOU THINK HE CAN
HOLD ONTO THAT AFTER HE
ANNOUNCES ON THURSDAY, OR IS
THURSDAY GOING TO BE THE BEST
DAY OF HIS CAMPAIGN AND EVERYONE
WILL PYLON?
>> Bret: I THINK THAT'S REALLY
THE BIGGEST QUESTION AND A LOT
WILL DETERMINE HOW HE HANDLES
THIS EARLY TIME.
BEING ON TV AND BOUNCING A
OHIO, NEW HAMPSHIRE AND
ELSEWHERE FOR A WHILE.
I THINK THIS LAUNCH WAS A
COMBINATION OF BOTH BAD
REPORTING AND MAYBE SOME BAD
STAFF WORK THAT WE THOUGHT WAS
GOING TO BE WEDNESDAY.
WE THOUGHT IT COULD BE
CHARLOTTESVILLE, VIRGINIA, AND
NOW THERE WAS A DECISION THAT
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE SOME OF
THAT.
>> THE VIDEO ROOM LAUNCH OUT OF
THE UNION HALL, OBVIOUSLY MAKING
A BIG MESSAGE IS WHERE THE MIC
DECIDING WHERE HE'S GOING TO GO
WITH THAT.
WHEN HE A COUPLE WEEKS AGO WAS
GOING THROUGH ALL THE QUESTIONS
ABOUT HIM BEING TOO TOUCHY,
THERE WERE QUESTIONS LIKE, WHY
IS PRESIDENT OBAMA NOT COMING
OUT TO DEFEND HIM?
PRESIDENT REAGAN DID NOT COME
OUT UNTIL AFTER THE PRIMARY
PROCESS WAS FINISHED FOR 41 WHEN
HE WAS RUNNING AND BILL CLINTON
DIDN'T DO THAT EITHER FOR
AL GORE.
I GUESS THE FORMER PRESIDENT
THINKS THAT THEY HAVE TO WIN IT
ON THEIR OWN?
>> I THINK PRESIDENT OBAMA WILL
STAY BACK AS FAR AS THE
ENDORSEMENT OF ONE CANDIDATE.
I THINK THE QUESTION MORE WAS A
CHARACTER ASSASSINATION, AND
WHAT THERE BE -- USE A LISTEN.
JOE IS LIKE THAT.
I'M NOT ENDORSING HIM AS
PRESIDENT BUT I'M ENDORSING HIM
AND HIS CHARACTER.
I THINK THE OBAMA FOLKS MAY BE
SPLIT AND I'M NOT SURE THAT
PRESIDENT OBAMA WILL ENDORSE
JOE BIDEN IN THE END.
>> Dana: YOU DON'T THINK EVEN
AT THE END, LIKE IF HE WERE TO
SECURE THE NOMINATION?
>> Bret: OF COURSE IF HE
SECURES THE NOMINATION.
>> Dana: MY LAST QUESTION,
MAYOR PETE, HE JUST ANNOUNCED
THERE WOULD BE A TOWN HALL.
>> Bret: YES MAY 19 WITH
CHRIS WALLACE.
THAT WILL BE A GREAT TOWN HALL,
AND WE HAVE BERNIE SANDERS, AMY
KLOBUCHAR IS COMING UP WITH
MARTHA AND ME IN MILWAUKEE ON
MAY 8TH AND THEN, MAY 19TH IS
MAYOR PETE.
>> Dana: WE WILL HAVE TO GET
JOE BIDEN ON THE BANDWAGON.
BRET BAIER, THANK YOU.
FOX NEWS ALERT ON A NEW TWIST IN
THE SMOLLETT CASE.
TWO OFFICERS WHO THEY■y■■■■■■■==
'S FIRING A LAWSUIT AGAINST
THE ATTORNEYS.
>> NOW, THE TWO WHO CARRIED OUTS
HOAX DIRECTED BY THE ACTOR
JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
THE SUIT CLAIMS THAT AFTER THE
CHARGES WERE■ROPPED, THEY DID
APPEARANCES ON NEWS PROGRAMS AND
PODCASTS AND DEFEND THEIR
BROTHERS.
THE SUIT SAYS THE LAWYERS EXIT
STOMACH AND SAIDJJJJ
EXECUTED A HATE CRIME AND WORE
WHITE FACE.
THEY ALSO CAUSE EMOTIONAL
DISTRESS.
AND AND, THAT'S CLAIMING THEY
WERE DOING SOMETHING SUCCESSFUL.
THEY INFERRED THAT ON THE
PODCAST "REASONABLE DOUBT" THAT
THE YOUNGER BROTHER ENGAGED AT
LEAST BRIEFLY IN HOMOSEXUAL ACTS
WITH SMOLLETT.
AT THE BROTHERS SAY THAT IS
FALSE.
BUT GETTING TO THE RECORDS PUT
SOMETHING ON BACKGROUND, A
THEORY FOR WHY THE BROTHERS■=■=E
WAS NOT.
IT'S BEEN ONE OF MIK YOU
FOR FOLLOWING UP ON THAT.
WE'LL KEEP AN EYE ON IT.■Ãs@s@B■
JOE BIDEN'S EXPECTED 2020
ANNOUNCEMENT.
I HAD TO COME UP WITH HER ALL
THE WAITING HELPS OR HURTS HIM
WITH THE VOTERS.
AND WHY AUTHORITIES AND■ú■ú■■■;■
ARE WARNING, THE VIOLENCE IS NOT
OVER.
>> THEY ARE NOT TALKING.
ANRE AFR
for up to 100% of
your home's value.
So if you need money
for your family,
call NewDay USA.
With Automatic Authority
from the VA,
we can say yes when
banks say no.
call 1-833-844-6702
I have fantastic news for
veteran homeowners
who need cash.
With home values rising all
across the country,
now's the time to use your
valuable VA home loan benefit.
NewDay USA can
help you refinance
and get 54,000 dollars
or more and
lower your payments
by 600 dollars a month.
And since they've been granted
Automatic Authority by the VA,
NewDay can say yes
when banks say no.
So if you're a veteran
homeowner who needs cash,
now's the time to
call NewDay USA.
Go to NewDayUSA.com
or call 1-833-844-6702
I don't keep track of regrets.
I never count the wrinkles.
And I don't add up the years.
But what I do count on...
is staying happy and healthy.
So, I add protein,
vitamins■ BOOST®.rals to my die
Delicious BOOST®
High Protein Nutritional Drink
has 20 grams of protein,
along with 26 essential
vitamins and minerals
your body needs.
All with guaranteed great taste.
The upside-
I'm just getting started.
BOOST® High Protein.
Be Up For Life™.
Look for savings on BOOST®
in your Sunday paper.
You're headed down the
highway when the guy in
front slams on his
brakes out of nowhere.
You do, too, but not in time.
Hey, no big deal.
You've got a good record
and Liberty Mutual
won't hold a grudge by raising
your rates over one mistake.
You hear that, Karen?
Liberty Mutual
doesn't hold grudges.
How mature of them!
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>> Dana: IN JUST TWO DAYS,
JOE BIDEN WILL BE■■■■■■■■ OFFICN
THE 2020 DEMOCRATIC RACE.
DELIBERATIONS BACK AND FORTH
ABOUT HIS ANNOUNCEMENT AFFECTED
HIS ROLLOUT.
MASTER OF COMMUNICATIONS, WE
WANTED TO GET YOUR TAKE ON THIS.
DO YOU THINK THIS WAS A PROBLEM
THAT HE'S ON-AGAIN, OFF-AGAIN OR
MAYBE WE WERE KEPT IN THE DARK
BUT HE'S GOING TO BE IN ON
THURSDAY?
>> I THINK IT'S A PROBLEM.
PEOPLE TENDED TO WANT THE OPTION
THAT THEY DON'T HAVE AND THEN
THEY GET THE OPTION, AND THEY
SAY, I'M DISAPPOINTED.
THAT COULD'VE BEEN HANDLED
DIFFERENTLY.
BUT I THINK THAT IS A SHORT-TERM
PROBLEM.
I ALSO THINK A SHORT-TERM
PROBLEM IS BIDEN THIS JUGGERNAUT
IS GOING TO GET IN THE RACE AND
HE WILL FIND HIMSELF TALKING
ABOUT BACK MASSAGES AND HE WILL
TRY TO TALK ABOUT SERIOUS ISSUES
AND THE MEDIA AND THE PUBLIC ARE
GOING TOj> SAY, ABOUT THOSE BACK
MASSAGES.
IN ONE OF THE REASONS THAT
HAPPENS, IF WE WANT IT TO
HAPPEN, WE WAN
AANDIDATE C TAKE HIS
BEATING.
THAT I THINK IT'S A BAD NEWS FO
HIM.
I THINK THE GOOD NEWS FOR HIM IS
ENTERING A CLIMATE WHERE THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY HAS BASICALLY
BECOME THIS VICTIM'S JUBILEE AND
IF HE CAN STANDUT AMONG THESE
DRIVEN THAT CAN GIVS TO
DEMOCRATIC■& VOTER AND GIVE THEM
THE OPTION.
>> IT'S LIKE, HE'S RUN MANY
TIMES AND THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
HAS TRANSFORMED EVEN JUST IN A
FEW YEARS SINCE BARACK OBAMA AND
JOE BIDEN WERE IN THE
WHITE HOUSE.
HE'S GOING TO BE ASKED, HAVE YOU
MISSED YOUR MOMENT?
AND HOW DO YOU ANSWER SOMETHING
LIKE THAT?
>> SURPRISE IS ALWAYS BETTER.
IT GETS BACK TO THE SEINFELD AND
"THE SOPRANOS" ENDING.
THE FACT THAT WE SPEND A YEAR
WAITING FOR THE ENDING, WE ARE
GUARANTEED DISAPPOINTMENT.
I THINK THAT BIDEN'S BEST OPTION
IS TO NOT SPEND TOO MUCH TIME
ADDRESSING IT AND TALKING ABOUT
THINGS THAT PEOPLE ARE WORRIED
ABOUT AND I THINK HIS CHALLENGE
IS GOING TO BE, HE'S GOING TO
WANT TO BE A STATESMAN IN AN ERA
WHO COULD CARE LESS ABOUT
STATESMEN.
HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO GET BACK
TO THIS GUTTER STUFF THAT HE
REALLY DOESN'T WANT.
I THINK ONE THING THAT HE'S GOOD
AT IS WHAT WE DO IN OUR BUSINESS
WHICH IS TRANSITIONING.
WE DON'T REALLY SPEND A LOT OF
TIME TALKING ABOUT THINGS THAT
YOU DON'T FEEL LIKE TALKING TO
AND GET TO THE THINGS THAT YOU
WANT TO TALK ABOUT AND THAT
EVENTUALLY WILL HAPPEN.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT DEMOCRATIC
SUPPORTERS WHICH ARE WAITING IN
THE WINGS TO ENDORSE SOMEONE
WILL DO SO RIGHT AWAY OR WILL
THEY WAIT AND WATCH THIS PRIMARY
PROCESS PLAY OUT?
>> I THINK THEY HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL IT PLAYS OUT BECAUSE
NOBODY THOUGHT THAT TRUMP WOULD
EMERGE SUCCESSFULLY FROM THE
PRIMARY PROCESS AND IT'S NOT AS
YOU SAID BEFORE THE BREAK
HISTORICALLY, SITTING PRESIDENTS
DON'T COME OUT AND EMBRACE THEIR
PARTY'S CANDIDATE.
THAT'S MUCH CLOSER UNTIL THE
END.
RE OPERATING IN A CLIMATE TO
ASK OURSELVES QUESTIONS.
IF BIDEN WAVES HIS HAND IN THE
WRONG DIRECTION PEOPLE SAY WHAT
DID THAT MEAN?
WHEREAS I DON'T THINK PEOPLE DID
THAT 30 YEARS AGO.
>> Dana: THE OTHER QUESTION
HE'S GOING TO BE ASKED IS, ARE
YOU TOO OLD TO RUN?
WHAT'S THE WAY TO COMBAT THAT IF
YOU ARE BIDEN.
IS IT SHOW, NOT EXPLAIN?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I THINK WHERE REAGAN KILLED THAT
IS EVERYBODY WAS EXPECTING AND
ELDERLY DODDERING FIGURE BUT
WHEN YOU SAW THAT IN ACTION, HE
DIDN'T LOOK THAT WAY AND HE
DIDN'T SOUND THAT WAY.
I THINK HE COMES ACROSS AS A LOT
YOUNGER.
I THINK THE OTHER THING HE HAS
GOING FOR HIM DESPITE ALL OF THE
BACK MASSAGE TALKS IS, HE HAS A
REAGAN QUALITY WHERE PEOPLE MAY
EVENTUALLY SAY HE DOES STUFF
LIKE THAT.
I REMEMBER IN MY EARLY 20s AS
A YOUNG AIDE IN REAGAN'S
WHITE HOUSE, WHEN REAGAN WOULD
SAY SOMETHING LIKE TREES CAUSE
POLLUTION, THE DEMOCRATS THOUGHT
THAT WAS THE END OF THE WORLD
AND EVERYONE ELSE SAID, HE JUST
DOES STUFF LIKE THAT.
I DON'T THINK IN THE END BIDEN'S
BEHAVIOR RISES TO THE WEINSTEIN
LEVEL AND I THINK THAT MAYBE ONE
THING HE HAS GOING FOR HIM.
>> Dana: ARGUE AGING IN
REVERSE.
IF YOU WERE IN THE EARLY 20s
IN THE REAGAN ADMINISTRATION?
>> YES, I WAS AN EMBRYO.
STATEMENT OF THANK YOU.
I HAD, WHAT CAUSES MORE HARM TO
THE COUNTRY THAN RUSSIA'S
ELECTION INTERFERENCE?
CLUSTERED FELONS AND TERRORISTS
HAVE THE RIGHT TO VOTE WHILE
BEHIND BARS?
WHY 12020 CONTENDERS SAYS, YES.
tched for value.
For family.
For power.
It was time to upgrade.
I switchedm to Chevy.
For power.
See why people are
switching to Chevy.
We love our Chevy.
I love my
Malibu.
My Colorado.
My Camaro.
My Traverse.
Why did we switch?
Just look at it.
♪♪
(ding)
Hey, who are you?
Oh, hey Jeff, I'm a car thief...
What?!
I'm here to
steal your car because,
well, that's my job.
■
What?
What??
WHAT?!
(laughing)
What??
WHAT?!
What?!
[crash]
WHAT?!
Haha, it happens.
And if you've got
cut-rate car insurance,
paying for this could
feel like getting robbed twice.
So get Allstate...
and be better protected
from Mayhem...
like me.
♪
Ok everyone!
Our mission is to
provide complete,
balanced nutrition
for strength and energy!
Whoo-hoo!
tasting Ensure.
balanced nutrition
for strength and energy!
With nine grams of protein
and twenty-six vitamins
and minerals.
Ensure, for strength
and energy.
>> Dana: SRI
PRIME MINISTER'S WARNING THERE
ARE MORE MILITANTS AND
EXPLOSIVESHERE FOLLOWING
THE DEADLY EASTER TERROR
ATTACKS.
ISIS CLAIMS
RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE BOMBINGS
IL MORE THAN 320
PEOPLE.
MEANWHILE, WE GET OUR FIRST LOOK
AT THE CHILLING MOMENTS BEFORE
■÷■■CKER STROLLED INTO A
CATHOLIC CHURCH SERVICE AND
DETONATED A BOMB STRAPPED TO HIS
BACK.
WHAT IS THE SITUATION THERE NOW,
REBECCA?
>> A CARTIER HAS BEEN OPPOSED
AGAIN IN THE EARLY HOURS OFy;■M.
YOU CAN T■;■;x; THAT S■;
ISN'T JUST IN SHOCK, PEOPLE HER;
ARE JUST STILL■ IN FEAR OF
FURTTA
THERE HAVE BEEN THOSE COMMENTS
THAT CAME OUT FROM T■
PRIME MINISTER WHERE HE DID SAY
THAT PEOPLE WERE ON THE RUN,
SUSPECTS, AND THERE ARE
EXPLOSIVES OUT THERE.
AN51SO HEARD■ÑÑ THAT■#■#
THEY WERE SEARCHING FOR A VAN
EXPLOSAS SUSPECTED OF CONTAININp
AT■■ NO MORE THAN
300 PEOPLE HAVE BEEN KILLED
INCLA FOREI■I",■á NATIONALS,■ AD
FOLLOWING THIS, IT'S CLEAR THAT
THE SITUATION IS ONGOING
INSECURITY IS VERY TIGHT AROUND
THE SERIAL LINK AT THE MOMENT.
>> Dana: WHAT WE KNOW SO FAR
ABOUT WHO MIGHT BE BEHIND THE
ATTACKS, IS ISIS REALLY
RESPONSIBLE?
>> THEY HAVE NOT COME FORWARD
AND CLAIMED THE ATTACK AND
THERE'S NOT REALLY EVIDENCE AS■.
THEY DID PUT A VIDEO UP ON THEIR
WEBSITE, WHICH APPEARS TO SHOW
WHAT THEY SAY, BASICALLY THE
ATTACKERS ARE AND, THE
PRIME MINISTER HAS NOT RUL■@■@■T
THE POSSIBILITY THAT ISIS ARE
CONNECTED TO THIS, THE
GOVERNMENT ACTUALLY NAMED A
LOCAL GROUP, JIHADIST GROUP
E MIND THE
GOVERNMENT HAVE SPOKEN ABOUT
INTERNATIONAL INVOLVEMENT AND
THERE DEFINITELY SEEMS TO BE■■■■
■■SOME KIND OF INTERNATIONAL
SUPPORK BEHIND THI■>■>■>■>'VE MQ
TRAINING.>> Dana: THAT'S AN INTG
DETAIL.
THANK YOU FOR THE REPORT.
MEXICAN OFFICIALS ARE STEPPING
UP ENFORCEMENT AGAINST A MIGRANT
CARAVAN MAKING ITS WAY TO THE
BORDER.
THIS COMES AFTER INCREASED
PRESSURE FROM THE UNITED STATES.
LIVE UPDATE NEXT.
PLUS, A SUPREME COURT JUSTICE
DISCUSSING WHETHER A CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION CAN BE INCLUDED IN THE
CENSUS.
ACTING DHS SECRETARY WILL WEIGH
IN AND HE IS HERE.■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
.
We all need to plan,
for 18 years or more,
i■■■i■■■■■■qqqq■■■■■■■■!qt.
I don't have a
whole lot saved up,
but I'm working on it now.
I will do  to do.
Plan your financial
life with Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
>> Dana: HUNDREDS OF
SOUTH AMERICAN MIGRANTS ON THE
WAY THROUGH MEXICO HAVE BEEN
■8■8 THEIR WAY TO
TH BORDER.
IT'S THE LARGEST SINGLE RAID ON
A CARAVAN SINCE A GROUP STARTED
MAKING THEIR WAY THROUGH MEXICO
LAST YEAR.
JONATHAN, HOW DID THIS PLAY OUT?
>> IT APPEARED TO BE A CONCERTED
EFFORT BY MEXICAN AUTHORITIES TO
SEND A SIGNAL THAT THEY WILL NO
LONGER BE SO ACCOMMODATING TO
THE THOUSANDS OF
FROM CENTRAL AMERICA AND HEADI■■
TO THE U.S. BORDER.
■■O■ HEREK7
YOU SEE THERE, THE MIGRANTS
GHTING BACK WITH STICKS AS
POLICE BEGAN A CLEARLY
WELL-PLANNED OPERATION ISOLATING
A GROUP FROM HUNDREDS OF
EXHAUSTED MIGRANTS AS THEY TOOK
A BREAK IN THE SHADE.
OFFICERS GRABBING MEN, WOMEN AND
CHILDREN TAKING THEM AWAY TO
WAITING BUSES.
SEPARATELY I ALSO WANTED TO SHOW
THIS VIDEO FOR YOU.
THIS WAS GIVEN TO YOU BY THE
CUSTOMS AND BORDER PROTECTION
OFFICIALS.
WHAT IT SHOWS THEY SAY WAS SHOT
ON THE ARIZONA MEXICO BORDER AND
SHOWS HEAVILY ARMED SMUGGLERS.
CBP SAYS IT IS A VERY CONCERNED
TO SEE THOSE SORT OF WEAPONS IS
NOW BEING BY HUMAN SMUGGLERS
RIGHT ON THE BORDER AS YOU CAN
SEE VERY PLAINLY THERE.
THE WOMAN AND HER SON BY THE WAY
WERE QUICKLY DETAINED BY CBP
AGENTS.
THOSE ARMED SMUGGLERS ARE STILL
AT LARGE SOMEWHERE IN MEXICO
DANA.
>> Dana: AND WITHOUT OTHER
STORY WITH MILITIA OPERATING ON
THE SIDE OF THE BORDER, WHAT'S
THE LATEST ON THAT?
>> THE LEADER OF THAT GROUP HAS
ANOTHER DATE IN COURT ON MONDAY.
LARRY HOPKINS WAS HELD ON
FIREARMS CHARGES.
AND HOLDING THEM UNTIL REAL
BORDER PATROL AGENTS COULD EVEN
GET THERE.
200 ON REGULAR ARMED MILITIAS
CURRENTLY OPERATING ON THE
SOUTHWEST BORDER.
THAT WENT ON "UNDER THE GUISE OF
CITIZENS PATROLS SUPPORTING CBP.
AS WE REPORTED HERE YESTERDAY,
THEY SET IN THE WEEK, THAT
CITIZENS SHOULD NOT BE TAKING
THE LAW INTO THEIR HANDS AT ANY
POINT AND IT SHOULD LEAVE A
LAW ENFORCEMENT ALONG THE BORDER
TO HAVE THE APPROPRIATE
GOP■ AGENCIES.
>> Dana: JONATHAN HUNT,
THANK YOU.
IT COULD BE THE SUPREME COURT'S
BIGGEST CASE THIS TERM.
THERE IS ANB APPEAL OVER WHETHER
A CITIZENSHIP QUESTION COULD BE
INCLUDED IN A 2020 CENSUS.
THANKS FOR JOINING US HERE■■.
CAN I START WITH THAT QUESTION
THAT IS BEING POSED TON■ THE
SUPREME COURT?
DO YOU SUPPORT THE IDEA OF
ASKING A CITIZENSHIP QUESTION ON
THE CENSUS?
>> THEY MADE IT CLEAR, IT'S
GOING TO BE UP TO THE
SUPREME COURT TO DECIDE WHETHER
WE CAN MOVE FORWARD ON
>> TO JONATHAN'S REPORT, IT
SEEMS TO ME THAT THE MEXICAN
LEGAL AUTHORITIES ARE DOING
MORE, AND THAT'S BECAUSE OF THE
PRESSURE THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
HAS TRIED TO PUT ON THE MEXICANS
TO DO SOMETHING.
>> WE ARE DEALING WITH ORIGINAL
PHENOMENON.
SO ANY SOLUTION WE ARE GOING TO
HAVE TO REDUCE THE FLOW IS GOING
TO RELY.
AND WE ASKED■■-■ FOR AND PROCEED
THAT INTRODUCTION OF THESE
LARGER GROUPS.■■■■■■■■
THAT'S A REPORT THAT THE
SMUGGLERS HAD, AND OUR BORDER
PATROL AGENTS.
HIGH-CAPACITY RIFLES FOR YEARS
AND WE ARE PREPARED TO ENCOUNTER
THAT.
WE HAVE SPECIAL TEAMS, OUT AND
OPERATING WHERE WE HAVE AREAS OF
CARTEL ACTIVITY AND BANDIT
ACTIVITY.
BUT THAT IS A CONCERN IS
COURTING A WOMAN AND A CHILD
ACROSS MULTIPLE HEAVILY ARMED
MEN.
YOU WONDER WHAT'S GOING ON■■■■■■
THEM NORTHERN PART OF MEXICO.
>> Dana: DO YOU PLAN TO ASK
FOR MORE TROOPS FROM THE
PENTAGON TO HELP YOU AT THE
BORDER?
>> WE HAVE A ROBUST PARTNERSHIP,
AND FREEING UP AGENTS TO UNDO
THEIR AGENCIES.
THEY HAVE HELPED US REPEL TO
ATTEMPTS BY CARAVAN TO ENTER THE
UNITED STATES BY HELPING US
FORTIFY A FORCE OF ENTRY.
WE WILL CONTINUE TO LOOK AT WAYS
WHERE THE DOD AND THEIR MISSION
AND FUNCTIONS, AN END THEY
ALREADY ARE ENGAGED.
AND WITH DOD FUNDING, WE WILL BE
G
IT'S BEEN ONE OF THE ABOUT
WALL.■
THE WALL IS BEING RAPIDLY B,
K■■■■■■■■■■■■■o■o■o■o■■■
SOME TRU SUPPORTERHE
WALLS NOT BEING BUILT.
HOW DO YOU PLAN TO COMBAT THAT
IF YOU CAN'T GET CONGRESS TO
APPROPRIATE ANY ADDITIONAL MONE
MONEY?
IT'S ALREADY BEEN BUILT, IN LESS
THAN TWO YEARS.
THAT SHOWS HOW AGGRESSIVELY WE
ARE MOVING OUT ON THIS.
WITH THE EXPANDED WITH THE ARMY
CORPS OF ENGINEERS AND BUILDING
WALL WHERE OUR BORDER PATROL
AGENTS ON TDSo■■■o■■■■■HEY
NEEDED, WE WILL SHOW A LOT OF
PROGRESS THIS.>> DHAT ABOUOU
HAVE A GOOD RELATIONSHIP WITH
MEMBERS ON THE HILL.
YOU'VE WORKED IN THE FIELD FOR A
LONG TIME, WHAT ARE THE TWO
THINGS THAT YOU THINK YOU NEED
FROM CONGRESS THAT YOU MIGHT BE
ABLE TO GET DONE THAT HELPS
ACTUALLY ADDRESSED THE PROBLEM?
>> I WOULD REFER TO A RECENT
REPORT.
THIS WAS A BIPARTISAN GROUP OF
EXPERTS THAT RODE ON NONPARTISAN
REPORT THAT THEY DECIDED WAS AN
EMERGENCY.
WE HAVE A CRISIS ON THE BORDER,
AND WE NEED TO CHANGE OUR LEGAL
FRAMEWORK AND OUR STRENGTH AND
IMMIGRATION LAWS TO MAKE US
EFFECTIVE.
>> Dana: BUT IF YOU CAN'T GET
THE COMPREHENSIVE IMMIGRATION
REFORM, IS THERE SOMETHING MORE
SPECIFIC THAT YOU COULD USE?
>> THERE IS.
THE TWO TARGETED AREAS WE NEED
TO, THAT'S A FEW SENTENCES OF
LAW.
AND SECONDLY THE ABILITY TO HAVE
UNACCOMPANIED CHILDREN OR BE
ENTICED INTO THE SMUGGLING
CYCLE, BEING ABLE TO REPATRIATE
THEM
>> ALSO ME ASK YOUúBOUTú
WHEN I WAS DOJ INHERE
YOU ARESPONSIBLE FOR
HELPING TO PROTECT AMERICA FROM
CYBER ATTACKS.
WE KNOW RUSSIA WAS TRYING TO
INTERFERE.
>> SO DHS HAS A BROAD SET OF
RESPONSIBILITIES.
I STARTED MY DAY IN
NEW YORK CITY TALKING ABOUT
THINGS THAT WE COULD DO TO
PREPARE FOR THE 2020 ELECTION
CYCLE, STATE AND LOCAL
GOVERNMENTS, AND WE ARE FOCUSED
ON THE 2020 PREPARATION.
OUR CYBER SECURITY AND
INFRASTRUCTURE SECURITY AGENCY
IS DIALED IN ON THIS ISSUE AND
WORKING WITH ALL 50 STATES.
>> Dana: BECAUSE IN THE
MUELLER REPORT THEY DID SAY THEY
COULDN'T CHANGE THE VOTES.
AT >> WE AWARE OF ANY -- BUT WE
HAVE TO BE VIGILANT AND PROTECT
o■o■AG.
E IS A LOT OF ACTING, AND
YOU ARE DOING A GREAT JOB.
IN TERMS OF STAFFING UP THE
DEPARTMENT AND THE THINGS THAT
YOU NEED TO, YOU HIRED 118
BORDER AGENTS IN 2018.
IT DO YOU NEED MORE OF THOSE AND
HOW DO YOU GET THEM IN THE JOB?
>> FIRST OF ALL ON THE
LEADERSHIP LEVEL, THE STRENGTH
OF DHS AS OUR PEOPLE.
I ASKED THE DEPUTY TO COME UP,
AND HE IS IN COAST GUARD.
WE HAVE A LOT OF EXPERIENCE AND
KNOW ALL OF OUR COMPONENT ENDS
VERY WELL ON A PERSONAL LEVEL.
BUT IN TERMS OF MORE PEOPLE,
BORDER PATROL AGENTS IS ONE OF
OUR TOP PRIORITIES.
AND MAKE SURE WE ARE RECRUITING
EFFECTIVELY.
>> YES.■■■■■■
>> Dana: THEEXT 2020
DEMOCRATS TAKING A STAND ON THE
COST OF HIGHER EDUCATION.
WHO WANTS TO CANCEL STUDENT
LOANS AND HOW MUCH IT WOULD
COST.
PLUS CAMPAIGN COMMITMENTS TO
RELAX RESTRICTIONS ON THE BORDER
MAKING IT EASIER FOR MIGRANTS TO
ENTER AND
STAY.
The NewDay VA Cash Out
Loan can help you
get over 50,000 dollars to pay
off  the credit card debt,
put cash in the bank,
and reduce your payments
by over 500 dollars a month.
And since NewDay's
been grantedUUUHHHH
Automatic Authority
by the VA,
they can say yes when
banks say no.
Get the fina■rity
you've earned and deserve.
Call 1-833-844-6706
■■■■■m8■8■%■%■E/E■E■■■■■■■■■■■■■
I never thought I'd say this
but I found bladder leak
underwear
that's actually pretty.
Always Discreet Boutique.
Hidden inside is a super
absorbent core
that quickly turns liquid to
gel.
So I feel protected and pretty.
Always Discreet Boutique.
I know that every single time
that I suit up,
there is a chance that's the
last time.
300 miles per hour, that's
where I feel normal.
I might be crazy
but I'm not stupid.
Having an annuity tells me
retirement is protected.
Annuities can provide protected
income for life.
Learn more at RetireYourRisk.org
>> ON THE FOX NEWS DECK, I LOOK
AHEAD TO.
THE FORMER HEAD OF A MAJOR DRUG
DISTRIBUTION COMPANY NOW GETS
HIT WITH CRIMINAL CHARGES.
PROSECUTORS SAY THIS IS A FIRST
CASE OF ITS KIND IN THE OPI
CRISIS IN AMERICA.
THE DEFENDANT IS VOWING TO FIGHT
TO HBREATH.
WE WILL HEAR FROM A LAWYER WHO
CALLS THIS A LONG OVERDUE
WARNING TO BIG
THAT AND THE REST OF TODAY'S■■W
NEWS WHEN THE NEWS ON AT
■THE TOP OF TODAY'S HOUR.
>> Dana: NOW FOR A LOOK AT THE
CAMPAIGN, HE'S CATCHING MANY
RIVALS OFF GUARD.
2020 CANDIDATES ARE LOOKING INTO
WHERE IT MIGHT BE VULNERABLE AND
ARE STRATEGIZING POTENTIAL LINES
OF ATTACK.
IN THE MEANTIME,
SENATOR ELIZABETH WARREN SAYS
SHE WILL NOT GET HILLARYED.
>> PEOPLE SAID TO ME, YOU ARE
GOING TO LOSE BECAUSE
MASSACHUSETTS IN 2011 ACCORDING
TO CONVENTIONAL WISDOM WAS NOT
READY TO HAVE A WOMAN SENATOR OR
GOVERNOR.
NOW YOU CAN IMAGINE HOW I HEARD
THAT.
I HEARD THAT AS, GET IN THIS
RACE.
RIGHT NOW, WHICH IS WHAT I DID.
>>  >> Dana: AMY KLOBUCHAR HAD
QUITE A CRINGEWORTHY MOMENT.
>> EVERY SINGLE TIME I HAVE A
RUN, I HAVE ONE EVERY SINGLE
CONGRESSIONAL DISTRICT IN MY
STATE INCLUDING MICHELLE
THAT WHEN YOU GUYS ARE
SUPPOSED TO■■o■o■o■o■o■o■o■.o■
>> THAT MOMENT OF COURSE SIMILAR
TO ONE■÷ú■ú■■■EB BUSH HAD DURING
THE PRIM■■■■ HEo■o■o■o■o■o■o■o■
UP AUDIENCE TO CLAP.
PLEASE CLAP.
SEVERAL DEMOCRATS DISCUSSING
LAST NIGHT DURING TOWN HALLS ON
ANOTHER NETWORK.
>> WE CAN'T HAVE COMPREHENSIVE
IMMIGRATION REFORM THAT WORKS
UNLESS IT ADDRESSES THE STATUS
FOR THOSE 11 SOME MILLION
UNDOCUMENTED IMMIGRANTS.
SO WHAT WE NEED TO DO IS MAKE
SURE THERE IS A PATHWAY TO
CITIZENSHIP FOR THEM ALSO.
FROM PROPERTY TAXES TO SALES
TAXES.
THE TRUTH IS, IN MANY RESPECTS
BECAUSE THEY ARE N ELIGIBLE
FOR A LOT OF BENEFITS, THEY ARE
SUBSIDIZING THE REST OF US.
>> THE EDITOR OF TownHall.com
AND JESSICA Tw■w■
FOONTRIBUTORT'ST TO H YOU THERE.
IMMIGRATION IS BIG OUT THERE AND
THE PATHWAY TO LET CITIZENSHIP,
IS THAT A LITMUS TEST?
>> I ACTUALLY THINK IT'S A
DISTRACTION FOR DEMOCRATS AWAY
FROM SOLVING THE CURRENT CRISIS
OF THE BORDER.
WHEN YOU SEE THOSE
CENTRAL AMERICAN FAMILIES COMING
AND YOU COME OFF INTO SOME BIG
FAN, IN FACT YOU ARE CREATING A
NEW ISSUE OF CITIZENSHIP IN TEN
OR 15 YEARS WHEN YOU HAVE ALL OF
THESE CHILDREN COME IN BY THE
CHILDREN
PARENTS ILLEGALLY THEN YOU GET
THE QUESTION OF WHETHER THEY CAN
STAY OR GO.
THE TALKING POINT OF
COMPREHENSIVE IMMIGRATION REFORM
DISTRACTS AWAY FROM HOW YOU
HANDLED THAT SITUATION NOW AND
HOWAKE SURE THIS CRISIS OF
A MILLION PEOPLE FLOWI
THE BORDER DOESN'T CONTINUE.
>> Dana: SO IS THIS THE FLOOR
LIKE YOU HAVE TO BE FOR THIS?
>> I THINK SO.
WHETHER IT'S HALFWAY TO
CITIZENSHIP, A MAJORITY OF
AMERICANS ARE SUPPORTIVE OF THA
THAT.
SO 100% I THINK THAT IS A LITMUS
TEST AND THE REAL TEST WILL BE
ONCE WE GET, AND WE DO GET
QUESTIONS ABOUT THE BORDER, HOW
YOU DEAL WITH THE ASYLUM SYSTEM
AND WHAT YOU THINK SHOULD BE
HAPPENING, WITH PEOPLE, I THINK
FOR NOW DEMOCRATS -- >>RE■■■■o■D
THIS WAS ABOUT FELONS AND VOTING
RIGHTS.
WATCH THIS.
>> DO YOU BELIEVE THAT PEOPLE
WITH FELONY RECORDS SHOULD BE
ALLOWED TO VOTE WHILE IN PRISON?
DOES THIS MEAN THAT YOU WOULD
SUPPORT IN FRANCHISING PEOPLE
LIKE THE BOSTON MARATHON BOMBER?
>> I THINK THE RIGHT TO VOTE WAS
INHERENT TO OUR DEMOCRACY.
YES, EVEN FOR TERRIBLE PEOPLE.
>> FOR PEOPLE CONVICTED AND
IMPRISONED, LIKE THE BOSTON
MARATHON BOMBER, THE YOU THINK
THEY SHOULD BE ABLE TO VOTE?
>> I THINK WE SHOULD HAVE THAT
CONVERSATION.
>> SHOULD PEOPLE CONVICTED OF
SEXUAL ASSAULT, THE
BOSTON MARATHON BOMBER, SHOULD
THEY BE ABLE TO VOTE WHILE
INCARC
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> Dana: WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF
THAT?
>> THE REACTION IN THE CROWD WAS
THE BIG DEAL HERE.
THEY POINTED OUT THIS MORNING
THATTIMATED
HOW IMPORTANT IT IS FOR
CANDIDATES TO TAKE THE POPULAR
POSITION EVEN IF IT DOESN'T
SOUND RIGHT FOR THEM.
IT SEEMS ANALOGOUS TO ME ALSO
THAT THE CONVERSATION WE HAD
ABOUT THIRD TRIMESTER ABORTION,
IT WAS A VERY COMFORTABLE ONE TO
HAVE.
I THINK IT'S A COMPLICATED ISSUE
AND IN VERMONT, THIS IS LEGAL.
WE'VE HAD A SUPREME COURT
DECISION, AND CITIZENSHIP IS NOT
A RIGHT THAT EXPIRES UPON
MISBEHAVIOR.
I WONDER IF -- INEQUITY IS THE
CORE PROBLEM HERE, IF YOU CAN
LOOK AT SOME SORT OF SYSTEM THAT
HAS THE SLIDING SCALE.
ALSO NEED TO TAKE INTO ACCOUNT
THAT PEOPLE IN PRISON ARE OFTEN
COUNTED INTO A POPULATION AND,
THE ELECTORAL COLLEGE IS NOT
INSTINCT -- I DON'T EVEN THINK
IT WAS PLANNING FOR THAT
QUESTION.
I'M VERY CURIOUS ABOUT THE BASE
AND THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY RIGHT
NOW IN THE PRIMARY PROCESS.
WHO IS WANTING T BOSTON BOMBER
TO BE VOTING FROM PRISON?
>> IT'S VERY DIFFERENT.
THERE IS A DEBATE TO BE HAD, IN
A CONVERSATION AS KAMALA HARRIS
WOULD SAY ABOUT WHETHER YOU GET
YOUR RIGHTS BACK ONCE YOU'VE
SERVED YOUR TIME.
I WOULD ASK DEMOCRATS IF THAT
ALSO APPLIES TO FIREARMS, PEOPLE
GET THEIR FIREARMS          BACE
SERVED TIME IN PRISON?
BUTN I'M JUST NOT SUREDE■■Ff■■■A
POLITICAL STRATEGY THERE.
>> I'M CURIOUS ABOUT THE KAMALA
HARRIS DECISION TO SAY, WE
SHOULD HAVE THAT CONVERSATION.
I MEAN, -- I BELIEVE IT ACTUALLY
TOOK A NUMBER OF HIM BY
SURPRISE.
BUT THAT WAS A CONVERSATION
RESTORING VOTING RIGHTS.
THEY ARE OVERWHELMINGLY PASSED
AND A LOT OF REPUBLICANS VOTED
FOR THAT AS WELL. YOU D■@ WATCHE
TOWN HALL, AND I DID IT, SHE
SAID SHE WAS READY TO HAVE A
CONVERSATION ABOUT A NUMBER OF
TOPICS AND SO I THINK THAT IS
SOMETHING THAT WILL CONTINUE ON
AND, THAT MAY HAVE BEEN --■ >>
THEN■a■a■■■■■■■3■0■■■■■3■■óóó■■.
HILLARY CLINTON SPEAKING JUST
MOMENTS AGO ABOUT THE MUELLER
REPORT AND WHAT SPEAKER PELOSI
SHOULD DO ABOUT THE IMPEACHMENT
QUESTION.
HER REACTION IS AHEAD.
PLUS SURVEILLANCE VIDEO SHOWING
AN ATTEMPTED CARJACKING.
HOW A GOOD SAMARITAN COMES TO
THE RESCUE.
♪ ♪
■■■■■■■■a■■ó■■■■g÷g■g■ga■■■■■
Alright, I brought in
Ensure Max Protein...
To give you
the Protein you need
with less of
the sugar you don't.
(Straining)
I'll take that.
(Cheers)
30 grams of protein
and 1 gram of sugar.
Ensure Max Protein.
In two great flavors.
Fact is, every insurance company
hopes you drive safely.■=■■;
But Alls■■??■■■■■■■...
with Drivewise.
It lets you know when you go too
fast...
With feedback to help you drive
safer.
Giving you the power to actually
lower your cost.
Unfortunatelñññ
anything about that.
Now that you know the truth...
are you in Good Hands?
>> Dana: AND NOW A LOOK AT OUR
DAILY THREE.
ROCHESTER DRUG COMPANY'S FORMER
CEO FACING DRUG CHARGES.
THEY'RE ACCUSED DISTRIBUTING
OXYCODONE.
THE WORLD'S FIRST MALARIA
VACCINE WILL BE GIVEN TO ABOUTi
360,000 CHILDREN IN THREE■■■■■■
SAYS THE VACCINE PREVENTS FOUR
IN TEN MALARIA CASES.
AN APPEALS COURT RULED
PHILADELPHIA CAN STOP REFERRING
FOSTER CHILDREN THE CATHOLIC
SOCIAL SERVICES FOR ITS REFUSAL
TO PLACE
CLINTON SPOKE OUT ABOUT THE
RELEASE OF THE REDACTED VERSION
■÷■÷ú■ú■ MUELLER REPORT IN A TA
AT THE TIME 100 SUMMIT.
DAVID LEE MILLER JOINS US WITH
MORE.
WHAT DID SHE HAVE TO SAY?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
SPEAKING HERE IN NEW YORK CITY
AT THIS TIMES SUMMIT HONORING
THE 100 MOST INFLUENTIAL PEOPLE
IN THE WORLD, HILLARY CLINTON
WAS ASKED ABOUT THE MUELLER
REPORT MOMENTS AGO.
SHE SAID THIS IS A STORY THAT
NEEDS TO BE TOLD OVER AND OVER
AGAIN.
LET'S LISTEN NOW TO SOME AFTER
WHAT SHE HAD TO SAY.
>> WE WERE THE SUBJECT OF A
FOREIGN ADVERSARY'S ATTACK, AN
ATTACK ON OUR ELECTION, AN
ATTACK ON OUR SOVEREIGNTY AND
OUR DEMOCRACY.
THIS IS NOT JUST ABOUT A
RECKONING WITH THE RECENT PAST,
THIS IS ABOUT WHAT IS GOING ON
TODAY AND THE THREATS TO OUR
NEXT ELECTION TO OUR DEFENSE AS
A NATION.
>> MRS. CLINTON SAID THIS IS NOT
THE END OF THE MATTER INVOKING
THE WORDS OF WINSTON CHURCHILL.
SHE SAID PERHAPS THIS IS THE END
OF THE BEGINNING.
THERE'S MORE TO FOLLOW.
>> Dana: JARED KUSHNER SPOKE AS
WELL?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE ALSO HEARD FROM JARED
KUSHNER, AN ADVISER TO THE
PRESIDENT.
HE DEFENDED THE ADMINISTRATION
IN THE WAKE OF THE MUELLER
REPORT.
SPEAKING AT THIS TIME EVENT, THE
ADVISER TO THE PRESIDENT, JARED
KUSHNER SAID THE INVESTIGATION
INTO THE RUSSIA INVOLVEMENT IN
THE ELECTION HE SAID WAS A
BIGGER PROBLEM THAN THE ACTUAL
MEDDLING.
LISTEN HERE.
>> QUITE FRANKLY IT'S A BIG
DISTRACTION TO THE Y.
LOOK AT RUSSIA DID BUYING
FACEBOOK ADS.
IT'S A TERRIBLE THING BUT I
THINK THE INVESTIGATIONS AND ALL
OF THE SPECULATION THE LAST TWO
YEARS HAS HAD A HARSHER IMPACT
ON OUR DEMOCRACY THAN A COUPLE
OF FACEBOOK ADS.
LOOK AT WHAT THEY ACCOMPLISHED,
THE ENSUING INVESTIGATIONS HAVE
BEEN MORE HARMFUL.
>> KUSHNER PLAYED THE
INVESTIGATION ON SOME PEOPLE'S
ABILITY TO ACCEPT MR. TRUMP WON
AND BLAME THE RUSSIANS.
IN HIS WORD, HE SAID WE SPENT
TWO YEARS GOING THROUGH THAT
NONSENSE.
>> Dana: DID KUSHNER HAVE ANY
OTHER NEWS?
>> INDEED.
HE WAS ASKED ABOUT A NUMBER OF
SUBJECTS INCLUDING A MIDDLE EAST
PEACE PLAN.
THE PLAN WON'T BE PRESENTED
UNTIL AFTER THE END OF RAMADAN.
HE CALLED IT A TOUGH PROBLEM.
WHILE HE DIDN'T GET INTO
DETAILS, HE SAID THE PLAN WOULD
TAKE WHAT HE CALLED AN
UNCONVENTIONAL APPROACH.
ON SAUDI ARABIA, THE U.S. WOULD
NOT DISPUTE THE ALLEGATIONS THAT
THE SAUDI CROWN PRINCE WAS
WORKING ON THE MURDER OF JAMAL
KHAISHOGGI.
HE CALLED FOR SCANNING ABILITY
AT ALL POINTS OF ENTRY.
FOR THE FUTURE, HE SAID
MR. TRUMP IS BUILD■@ FABULOUS
CAMPAIGN AND A NUMBER OF NEW
RESOURCES.
>> Dana: THANKS.
A HORRIFYING MOMENT CAUGHT ON
CAMERA.
A UTAH WOMAN WAS DRIVING WITH
THREE KIDS WHEN SHE SAW A MAN IN
THE ROAD.
SHE HONKED BUT HE TURNED AND
HEADED TOWARDS HER.
SHE PARKED AND TRIED TO LOCKED
THE DOORS.
SHE DIDN'T DO SO IN TIME.
THE GOOD NEWS IS, A GOOD