AND PHONY POSER
ENVIRONMENTALISM, TOO.
>> Tucker: THERE IS AN AWFUL
LOT OF THAT.
MARK STEYN, NOTHING PHONY ABOUT
MARK STEYN.
GREAT TO SEE YOU.
>> GREAT TO SEEWE YOU.
>> Tucker: WE ARE OUT OF TIME
BUT WE WILL BE BACK AND THAT IS
OURT PROMISE TO YOU.
TOMORROW NIGHT AT 8:00 P.M.
THE SHOW THAT IS THE SWORN ENEMY
OF LYING, POMPOSITY, SMUGNESS,
THAND GROUPTHINK.
DON'T GO AWAY, WE HAVE FANTASTIC
NEWS FOR YOU.
BY PREARRANGEMENT, SEAN HANNITY
WILL BE HOSTING THE 9:00 P.M.
SHOW.
>> Sean: AND 23 HOURS,
SURPRISINGLY, TUCKER IS GOING TO
BE BACK.
I HAD TO THINK ABOUT THAT ONE.
TUCKER, GREAT SHOW.
BUCKLE UP AND WELCOME TO
"HANNITY."
TONIGHT, MASS RAGE TOTALLY
CONSUMING THE MODERN DEMOCRATIC
SOCIALIST PARTY.
OF COURSE AFTER PRESIDENT TRUMP
WAS VINDICATED BY ROBERT MUELLER
AND FOR THE LEFT, IT IS LIKE A
ELECTION NIGHT 2016 ALL OVER
AGAIN BECAUSE FOR TWO AND A HALF
YEARS, DEMOCRATS ALONG WITH
THEIR PARTNERS IN THE MEDIA MOB
ARE PUMPING UP THEIR BASE.
THEY GET GIDDY AND PRAISED THEIR
HERO ROBERT MUELLER BECAUSE THEY
WERE FINALLY GOING TO GET
DONALD TRUMP.
IT'S LIKE THE EXIT POLLS SHOWED
HE WAS GOING TO LOSE AND THEY
WERE WRONG.
THE FACTS OF REALITY GOT IN THE
WAY BECAUSETH THERE NEVER WAS
COLLUSION, NO CONSPIRACY, NO
OBSTRUCTION FROM TRUMP AND HIS
CAMPAIGN.
NOW DEMOCRATS ARE DEFLATED AND
DOWNTRODDEN AND THEY ARE HITTING
LEVELS OF DELUSION WITH RECKLESS
FANTASIES ABOUT IMPEACHMENT AND
DOING EVERYTHING THEY CAN
POSSIBLY DO TO HARASS, EVEN USE
THE IRS AGAINST A SITTING
PRESIDENT.
TONIGHT, WE ARE EXPOSING IT
PIECE BY PIECE, AND WE ARE ALSO
GOING TO BE ASKING THE MOST
IMPORTANT UNANSWERED QUESTIONS.
BY THE WAY, THERE ARE HUNDREDS
OF THEM.
WE ARE GIVING YOU THE TOP ONES,
LIKE WHEN DID ROBERT MUELLER
KNOW THERE WAS NO COLLUSION, NO
COORDINATION?
WHY WEREN'T WE TOLD?
WHY DID THEY HOLD THAT BACK?
IF■■K■ THEY KNEW THERE WAS NO CE
ALL ALONG EARLY ON IN THE
INVESTIGATION, WHY NOT LET THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE, WE, THE PEOPLE>
KNOW?TO REVEAL TO WE, THE PEOPL,
THAT THIS WAS ALL BASED ON A W
SERIES OF FALSE NARRATIVES AND
PHONY ALLEGATIONS, LIKE THE
STEELE DOSSIER?
WHAT DIDN'T THEY INVESTIGATE
THIS WHICH, WAS LIKE A FINAL
NAIL DRILLED IN
ROBERT MUELLER?
BYRON YORK WRITES IN THE
"WASHINGTON EXAMINER" TODAY,
"IN THE WAKE OF THE MU
REPORT, THE QUESTION IS NOT
WHETHER THE DOSSIER'S CHARGES
WERE ACCURATE BUT WHY WERE THEYE
SO WRONG?"
EVEN OUR FRIEND BOB WOODWARD IS
ACKNOWLEDGING THE PROBLEMS WITH
CLINTON'S BOUGHT AND PAID FOR
RUSSIAN LIES USED IN THE
ELECTION.
I GUESS BETTER LATE THAN NEVER..
TAKE A LOOK.
>> EARLY IN BUILDING THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY
ASSESSMENT ON RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE, IN AN EARLY DRAFT,
THEY ACTUALLY PUT THE DOSSIER ON
PAGE TWO IN KIND OF A BREAKOUT
BOX.
I THINK IT WAS THE CIA PUSHING
THIS..
REAL INTELLIGENCE EXPERTS LOOKED
AT THIS AND SAID, NO, THIS IS
NOT INTELLIGENCE.
THIS IS GARBAGE AND THEY TOOK IT
OUT.
BUT IN THIS PROCESS THE IDEA
THAT THEY WOULD INCLUDE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT IN ONE OF
THE GREAT, STELLAR INTELLIGENCE
ASSESSMENTS, AS MUELLER ALSO
FOUND OUT, IS HIGHLY
QUESTIONABLE.
IT NEEDS TO BE INVESTIGATED.
>> Sean: HIGHLY QUESTIONABLE.
BOB, AGAIN, WE HAD AN ENSEMBLE
TEAM FOR OVER TWO YEARS, WE HAVE
BEEN PEELING THE LAYERS AFTER
LAYER AFTER LAYER OF THE BIGGEST
ABUSE OF POWER CORRUPTION
SCANDAL IN OUR HISTORY.
THIS ENSEMBLE CAST ON RADIO ANDg
TV AND MY SHOW, WE HAVE BEEN
RIGHT ALL ALONG AND NOW EVEN
"THE NEW YORK TIMES," EVEN THEY
ARE COMING TO TERMS WITH SOMES
DOSE OF REALITY, REVN A
NEW PIECE THAT THE DOSSIER IS
NOW UNDER RENEWED SCRUTINY.
BABY STEPS FOR THEM.
GET THIS: THE MEDIA MAY HAVE
BEEN MORE WRONG THAN WE THOUGHT■
ACCORDING TO "THE TIMES," THE
DOSSIER MAY HAVE BEEN A PART OF
A RUSSIAN DISINFORMATION
CAMPAIGN TO BEGIN WITH.
HILLARY'S CAMPAIGN, SHE PAID FOR
IT.
SET UP "LANDMINES AND SOW CHAOSO
AND DISCORD AMONG THE AMERICAN
ELECTORATE."
JOHN SOLOMON WILL JOIN US IN A
FEW MOMENTS TO EXPLAIN MORE TO
YOU BUT ASK YOURSELF, WHEN WILL
THE FAKE NEWS MEDIA MOB
APOLOGIZE FOR THEIR LIES AND
CONSPIRACY THEORIES?
■@ WILL THEY TAKEES?
■úCOUNTABILITY?
WHEN WILL THEY TAKE ACCOUNT FOR
FUELING COLLUSION, HYSTERIA,
BREATHLESS REPORTING?
DAY AFTER DAY, NIGHT AFTER
NIGHT.
IN THE MEDIA,
FACTS WERE ONLY AN AFTERTHOUGHT,
ANY ANONYMOUS SOURCE, YES, THEY
BELIEVED LIKE BUZZFEED'S
BOMBSHELL ABOUT THE PRESIDENT
HAVING THE PRESIDENT'S LIE WHICH
IS TOTALLY FALSE OR NPR BEING
EMBARRASSED AFTER IT LIED ABOUT
DON JR.'S SENATE TESTIMONY.
OR McCLATCHEY BLATANTLY WRONG
ABOUT MICHAEL COHEN'S TRIP TOPR.
IT NEVER HAPPENED.
"THE GUARDIAN" REPORTED A FAKE
CONSPIRACY ABOUT JULIAN ASSAGE.
THREE CNN EMPLOYEES FORCED TO
RESIGNEPORTING AN UNTRUE
RUSSIA-RELATED STORY ABOUT OUR
FRIEND, THE MOOCH, ANTHONY
SCARAMUCCI.
OR BRIAN ROSS LEAVING ABC AFTER
A FAKE NEWS STORY
I FOUND TRUMP IN RUSSIA
THAT ACTUALLY IMPACTED
NEGATIVELY THE STOCK MARKET.
IT WAS FAKE HYSTERIA ABOUT A
RUSSIAN SPY IN THE WHITE HOUSE
OR BLOOMBERG FORCED TO CORRECT
THEIR STORY ABOUT TRUMP
AND DEUTSCHE BANK.
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" WALKING
CLAIMS BACK ABOUT PAUL MANAFORT
SHARING POLLING DATA WITH THE
UTRUSSIAN OLIGARCH.
DON'T FORGET
"THE WASHINGTON POST" HAVING TO
CORRECT THEIR STORY ABOUT
RUSSIANS HACKING A VERMONT
UTILITY WHICH WASN'T TRUE.
IT WAS EVERY SECOND, EVERY HOUR,
EVERY DAY, FAKE STORY AFTER FAKE
STORY, LIE AFTER LIE, CONSPIRACY
AFTER CONSPIRACY THEORY.
RATHER THAN TAKE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR ALL OF THESE FAILURES, AN
EPIC FAIL, THE MEDIA IS SINKING
TO NEW LOWS.
DOUBLING DOWN ON LIES AND
STUPID.
LOOK AT HOW A SO-CALLED REPORTER
AT NBC NEWS LITERALLY AMBUSHED
ROBERT MUELLER AS HE IS LEAVING
EASTER SERVICES.
THESE PEOPLE HAVE NO SHAME.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> SIR, CAN I ASK YOU A COUPLE
OF QUESTIONS?
WILL YOU TESTIFY BEFORE
CONGRESS, SIR?
NO COMMENT.
>> ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
>> NO COMMENT.
>> IF HE WERE ANYBODY BUT THE
PRESIDENT, WHAT MR. TRUMP BE
INDICTED?
WHY DIDN'T YOU MAKE A
RECOMMENDATION TO CONGRESS ONE
WAY OR THE OTHER?
DID THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
ACCURATELY CHARACTERIZE YOUR
POSITIONS ON CONSPIRACY AND
OBSTRUCTION?
>> Sean: COULD WE MAKE
CHURCHES OUT-OF-BOUNDS?
KIDS OUT-OF-BOUNDS?
THE HYSTERIA, SO MANY
STUNANSWERED QUESTIONS.
THIS IS REALLY ONLY THE FIRST
CHAPTER IN WHAT MUST BE A
RECKONING FOR THE COUNTRY.
IF THIS COUNTRY IS TO SURVIVE,
IT IS THAT SERIOUS.
LITERALLY, WE WILL SHINE
THE LIGHT NOW ON THE TEN BIGGEST
AND THERE ARE HUNDREDS■■■■■■UNA.
WHEN DID THE FBI FIRST REALIZE
THAT THE DOSSIER WAS BOUGHT AND
PAID FOR BY HILLARY CLINTON AND
IF THEY KNEW IT, WHY DIDN'T
MUELLER INVESTIGATE THAT WHEN
ISSUE OF RUSSIAN■■■■■■ INTERFER?
HOW MUCH EXCULPATORY EVIDENCE
THEY GEORGE
■ POULOS, CARTER PAGE AND
DID THEY HIDE THAT INFORMATION
FROMX%X%X%é/■%é/
WE HAVE A QUESTION FOR JAMES
COMEY, WHY DID JAMES COMEY SAYX%
SIGNED THE FIRST WARRANT, IT WAS
THE
WHY DID HE SIGN IT, WHICH MEANS
HE APPROVED IT, ASSU IT'S
VERIFIED IN OCTOBER 2016, AND
TELL TRUMP, THEN
PRESIDENT-ELECT,
2017, TRUMP TOWER IN■/■/ANUARY,
IT IS SALACIOUS BUT UNVERIFIED?
BY THE WAY, WHY WERE STEELE'S
ANTI-TRUMP BIASES HID
FISA COURT?
LIKE HILLARY BOUGHT AND PAID FOR
THAT IN BIG BOLD LETTERS.
WHY WETEL OFFICIALS
LEAKING DETA THE RUSSIA
BEFORE EVER CORROBORATING
ANYTHING TO DO WITH COLLUSION?
NEXT QUESTION, DID JAMES COMEY
MISHANDLE CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
WHEN LEAKING MEMOS FROM HISNF
PRIVATE CONVERSATIONS WITH THE
PRESIDENT?
ANDS A BIG ONE.
OKAY, LET'S GO TO THE OBAMA
WHITE HOUSE.
WHAT DID SUSAN RICE, SAMANTHA
LET ME SEE, JENNAN AND
CLAPPER, WHAT DID THEYND
WHENY KNOW WHAT?
WHAT DID OBAMA KNOW AND WHEN DID
HE KNOW IT?
IF, AS L■k PETER
STRZOK WERE SAYING,HEY WERE
RUNNING THE WHOLE THING FROM THE
JUSTICEARTMENT?
CIA OR FBI, DID THEY ENGAGE OR
THE TRUMP TEAM TO SPY ON THEMAGT
BEFORE OPENING THE SO-CALLED
INVESTIGATION?
IN OTHER WORDS, DID THEY BYPASS
AMERICAN LAWS ABOUT ABUSING
INTELLIGENCE AND USING THE
OF INTELLIGENCE AGAINST
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE AND
OUTSOURCE THAT TO FRIENDLY
ALLIES AND GET INFORMATION THEY
WOULDN'T OTHERWISE GET?
MAYBE PLACES LIKE THE U.K. TO
GATHER EVIDENCE ON THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN OR MAYBE AUSTRALIA OR
ITALY.
DID THE CIA TRY TO PRESSURE OF
THE FBI INTO OPENING A■■■■■■■■■@
COE BEFORE THE
ELECTION?
WE DO NEED TO KNOW, CONSIDERING
IT WAS SO IMPORTANT, ISSUES LIKE
LOAN APPLICATIONS, TAXES, AND
WHO ELSE LIED TO CONGRESS?
WE KNOW ANDREW McCABE IS BEING
PROBED FOR A FALSE TESTIMONY BUT
HE ALSO SAID NO DOSSIER, NO FISA
WARRANT.
HIS TESTIMONY CONTRADICTS THATO
OF GLENN SIMPSON AT FUSION GPS.
SOMEBODY LIED, SOMEBODY TOLD THE
TRUTH, AND THAT ALL CONFLICTS
WITH WHAT BRUCE OHR SAID.
LET'S GO BACK TO LORETTA LYNCH,
WHAT DID SHE KNOW AND WHAT DID
KNOW IT?
JOHN BRENNAN, JAMES CLAPPER,
WHEN DID THEY KNOW WHAT?
WE ARE INCHING CLOSER AND CLOSER
TO JUSTICE, THERE IS NO STOPPING
THIS ABUSE OF POWER AND
CORRUPTION FROM BEING EXPOSED.
THAT I CAN PROMISE YOU TONIGHT.
IT IS TIME FOR TRANSPARENCY AND
ACCOUNTABILITY.
WE CANNOT LET THIS HAPPEN IN OUR
COUNTRY.
MY SOURCES ARE TELLING ME, IT IS
IT IS TIME TO DECLASSIFY THOSE
FISA) APPLICATIONS.
BRUCE OHR'S 302, WHICH WE CALL
THE BUCKET OF FIVE,
WE STILL HAVE THE IG HORWITZ, HE
IS EXPECTED LATER THIS SPRING
WITH HIS REPORT ON FISA ABUSE.
THE JOHN HUBER REPORT ON MAKING
YOUR VIEWS, THE GANG OF EIGHT
MATERIAL.
LET'S SEE IT ALL.
DEMOCRATS WANT TRANSPARENCY,
OKAY, ABSOLUTELY.
LET'S EXPOSE THE BIGGEST ABUSE
OF POWERPL CORRUPTION SCANDAL IN
OUR HISTORY.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE WILL BE
SHOCKED.
LET'S EXPOSE THE NEW RADICAL
DEMOCRATIC SOCIALIST PARTY,
STILL HELL-BENT ON
SPREADING LIES EVERY SECOND,
EVERY HOUR OF EVERY DAY.
A PUBLIC TRIAL.
WHEN THE DEMOCRATS AREN'T
FUELING THEIR UNHINGED HYSTERIA,
LET NOT YOUR HEARTS BE TROUBLED
BECAUSE THEIR COHORTS IN THE
HATE TRUMP MEDIA MOB PICK UP THE
SLACK.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> IF THE MAIN CONCERN HERE IS
THAT HE IS NOT GOING TO BE
CONVICTED BY THE SENATE,
DEMOCRATS MAY BE MAKING A BAD
POLITICAL CALCULATION.OT
>> IT'S NOT AS OF THE MUELLER
REPORT WAS A DUD.
IT HAS A LOT TO DO THAT
IMPLICATES A PRESIDENT IS AN
ACTUAL CRIMES.
>> I STILL HOPE THAT IN THIS DAY
AND AGE REPUBLICANS WILL SEE THE
FACTS AND WILL BE AS APPALLED AS
DEMOCRATS ARE.
>> THIS REPORT WAS COMPLETELY
EXPOSING OF UNFIT, IMPEACHABLE
BEHAVIOR.
>> AN INNOCENT MAN DOES NOT
SCREECH AND COMPLAIN.
>> SO MIGHT ASK, WHY HAVEN'T YOU
STARTED, WHYHY HAVEN'T YOU OPEND
AN IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY OR IN
FAIRNESS, IS THAT WHAT YOU ARE
DOING RIGHT NOW?
>> HOW MUCH DOES THE POLITICS
MATTER?
>> IMPEACHMENT GETS POLITICIZED
SO YOU HAVE A LEGAL CASE THAT
YOU BELIEVE THIS HAPPENS AND YOU
SHOULD DO IT BUT THE POLITICS
DICTATE SOMETHING ELSE.
HOW WILL THAT INFLUENCE THIS
DECISION?
IS THIS IN NANCY PELOSI'S HANDS?
>> Sean: WE KNOW DEMOCRATS
AREN'T INTERESTED IN THE TRUTH.
EVEN SPEAKER PELOSI DOWNPLAYING
IMPEACHMENT.
WRITING THERE ARE OTHER WAYS TO
HOLD THE PRESIDENT ACCOUNTABLE.
SHE SCARED T TO DEATH, KNOWING E
POLITICAL RAMIFICATIONS, THIS
WITCH HUNT CONTINUING WILL MEAN
FOR THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY IN■k■kR
POWER.
THOSE SENTIMENTS ECHOED BY
DEMOCRATIC LEADERS IN A CALL
■■■■■■EARLIER TODAY.
THAT IS NOT STOPPING THE RADICAL
BASE OF THE NEW EXTREME RADICAL
SOCIALIST DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
COLLUSION TRUTH HERE, THE
BIGGEST LIE OF THEM ALL,■■@■,■
ADAM THE COWARDLY SCHIFF SAYING
THE REPORT PROVED HIM RIGHT.
YOU CAN'T MAKE THIS STUFF UP AND
I WILL SAY IT AGAIN, YOU ARE
WELCOME ON THE SHOW ANYTIME.
YOU WANT A FULL HOUR AND I WILL
GIVE YOU THREE HOURS OF MY RADIO
SHOWWOULD LIKE, 650
STATIONS AND A BIG AUDIENCE.
CONGRESSMAN, YOU ARE WELCOME ANY
TIME.
THAT GOES FOR THE REST OF THEM
IF THEY WANT TO BE A PART OF IT.
AS WE CONTINUE ALONG, ANYBODY
THAT WANTS TO BE A PART OF THIS
PROGXPOSE THE LIES
OF PEOPLE LIKE THEM.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
HOW MUCH HURTING YOU ARE DOING
TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
THE REAL COLLUDED-ER IN ALL OFW
THIS IS ONLY ONE PERSON AND WE
HAVE EVIDENCE FOR IT, COMEDIC
GOLD.
HERE'S THIS ON TAPE.
COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA TO IMPACT
OUR ELECTIONS.
>> SHE MET WITH TRUMP.
SHE BROUGHT HIM RUSSIAN GIRL,
CELEBRITY,
ALSO KNOWN AS A PERSON WITH A
STRANGE REPUTATION.
>> HOW DO YOU SPELL HER NAME?
WHAT IS THE NATURE OF THE
KOMPROMAT?
>> THERE WERE PICTURES OF NAKED
TRUMP.
>> WAS VLADIMIR PUTIN MADE AWARE
OF THEWA AVAILABILITY OF THE
COMPROMISING MATERIAL?
>> YES, OF COURSE.
>> WE WILL BE BACK IN TOUCH WITH
YOU THROUGH OUR STAFF TO MAKE
ARRANGEMENTS TO OBTAIN THESE
MATERIALS FOR COMMITTEE AND FOR
THE FBI AND I APPRECIATE YOUEM
REACHING OUT TO US.
>> Sean: WHAT IS THE NATURE OF
THE KOMPROMAT?
NAKED TRUMP.
DID VLADIMIR PUTIN SEE IT?
OF COURSE.
VLADIMIR SEE IT.
YOU CAN'T MAKE THIS STUFF UP.
WE HAVE DEVIN NUNES, WE WARNED
ABOUT RUSSIA AND PUTIN,
HOSTILE ACTORS ON THE WORLD
STAGE.
DEVIN NUNES IN 2014 WARNED@1■  E
OBAMA ADMINISTRATION IT ALL
HAPPENED ON THEIR WATCH THAT
THIS WOULD HAPPEN IN 2016.
THIS IS WHO THEY ARE AND WHAT
THEY DO AND AFTER 30 PLUS YEARS
AFTER OUR GOVERNMENT BEING
HACKED, CAN WE PLEASE BUILD
DEFENSES TO BE UN-HACKABLE?
WE SHOULD ALL BE CONCERNED ABO
THE INTEGRITY OF OUR ELECTIONS
AND THE FACT THAT THIS
GOVERNMENT HAS BEEN HACKED
REPEATEDLY FOR DECADES BY
HOSTILE REGIMES.
WE NEED A TOP TO BOTTOM KILLERER
DEFENSE PROCEDURE AGAINST THESE
HACKERS.
THAT IS WHY HILLARY CLINTON'S
EMAIL SERVER IS A REAL THREAT TO
OUR SAFETY AND SECURITY.
WE BELIEVE THAT PLACE WAS HACKED
BY AT LEAST SIX FOREIGN
ENTITIES.
THIS WAS ALL WEAPONIZED IN THE
PRESS IN THE DEEP STATE TO
BLUDGEON DONALD TRUMP.
BEHIND THE CURTAIN, WE GOT LIES,
IT IS TIME TO INVESTIGATE THE
INVESTIGATORS.
THAT MEANS HILLARY CLINTON AND
THE FACT THAT THAT INVESTIGATION
WAS RIGGED AND THEN THEY TRIED
TO RIG THE PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION
AND UNDO A DULY ELECTED
PRESIDENT.
THE MEDIA WAS ALL THERE.
LET'S STICK TO THE FACTS AND NOT
RUSH TO JUDGMENT.
MAYBE THE MEDIA CAN SELF-REFLECT
AND NOT JUMP ONTO THE NEXT FAKE
NEWS STORY ABOUT THETH PRESIDEN,
ESPECIALLY COMMON SENSE AND HAVE
AMERICA WAKE UP TO THEIR LIES
AND SMEARS.
THEY ATTACKED HIM WITH
INVESTIGATIONS AND ANONYMOUS
SOURCES AND THANKFULLY HE IS
FIGHTING BACK.
JUST TODAY THE PRESIDENT FILED A
LAWSUIT AGAINST THE DEMOCRATS'
LATEST STUNT.
NOW THEY WANT TO EMBOLDEN THE
IRS AND RELEASE HIS TAXES,
EXPLAINING THAT THE BOY HAS NO
LEGITIMATE PURPOSE.
NOT ONCE DID HE INVOKE EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE.
1.5 MILLION DOCUMENTS.
EVEN DONALD McGAHN, THE
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL, 30 HOURS
BEFORE MUELLER.
DO YOU SEE WHAT ISTO GOING ON?
THEY ARE OUT OF IDEAS.EY
NO IDEAS FOR THE BETTERMENT OF
TH PEOPLE.
THEY SINK TO A PSYCHOTIC LOW AND
THIS IS ALL THEY THINK ABOUT.
WHEN THEY ARE NOT PUSHING
ENDLESS INVESTIGATIONS, NONSTOPT
FAR LEFT SOCIALISM OR
BLUDGEONING A 16-YEAR-OLD KID.
YOU WANT TO SEE RADICAL
SOCIALISM?
LOOK AT COMRADE MAYOR OF
NEW YORK CITY ANNOUNCING TO BAN
"INEFFICIENT STEEL AND GLASS
SKYSCRAPERS" FROM NEW WORK!
RETROFIT EVERY BIG BUILDING IN
NEW YORK.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> THE BIGGEST SOURCE OF
EMISSIONS IN NEW YORK CITY IS
BUILDINGS.
WE ARE PUTTING ON CLEAR,
STRONG MANDATES, THE FIRST OF
ANY CITY ON EARTH TO SAY TO
BUILDING OWNERS, YOU
HAVE TO CLEAN UP YOUR ACT AND
SAVE ENERGY.ND
IF YOU DON'T DO IT BY 2030 THERE
WILL BE SERIOUS FINES.
WE WILL BAN THE CLASSIC GLASS
AND STEEL SKYSCRAPERS, WHICH ARE
INCREDIBLY INEFFICIENT.
IF SOMEBODY WANTS TO BUILD ONE,
THEY COULD TAKE A WHOLE LOT OF
STEPS TO MAKE IT
ENERGY-EFFICIENT BUT WE WILL NOT
ALLOW WHAT WE USED TO SEE IN THE
PAST.
>> Sean: NO GLASS AND STEEL,
HOW WILL WE BUILD THOSE
BUILDINGS?
YOU CAN'T BUILD THOSE WITH
TIMBER BECAUSE THAT WOULD BE
KILLING A TREE.
NO GAS, NO OIL,
NO CARS, NO ENGINES, NO PLANES
BUT EVERYTHING IS FREE.
THEY DON'T EVEN MEET THESE
STANDARDS, THEY ARE SO OVER THE
TOP.
OCASIO-CORTEZ WANTS
EVERY BUILDING IN AMERICA
RETROFITTED.
WOW, WHO WILL PAY FOR THAT?
HERE WITH REACTION, THE AUTHOR
OF THE INTRODUCTION TO THE
MUELLER REPORT, ALAN DERSHOWITZ
AND "THE HILL"'S JOHN SOLOMON.
LET ME START WITH YOU, AND I
ESPECIALLY WANT TO GO OVER THE
MEDIA AND I KNOW, PROFESSOR, YOU
HAVE A LOT TO SAY ABOUT THIS AS
WELL.
>> THERE HAS BEEN A FEW
SUGGESTIONS MAYBE THE MEDIA
SHOULD APOLOGIZE.
I THINK IT HAS A MORE IMPORTANT
STEP TO TAKE FIRST.
IT NEEDS TO RETRACT THE STORIESS
THAT ARE NOW DEMONSTRABLY FALSE
ORDS DEMONSTRABLY UNPROVEN.
ONCE DECLARED DREW, NOW
DEMONSTRABLY PROVEN FALSE.
MUELLER'S REPORT LAYS BARE AT
LEAST A DOZEN OF WHAT I WOULD
CALL DIRTY DOZEN STORIES THAT
ARE CLEARLY FALSE AND SOME OF
THEM ARE IN BIG PUBLICATIONS
LIKE "THE NEW YORK TIMES," LIKE
CNN.
THE WRITING AND JOURNALISM IS
WHEN YOU ARE WRONG, ADMIT YOU
MARE WRONG, RETRACT A STORY, AD
MOVE ON.
THAT HASN'T HAPPENED IN MORE
THAN A DOZEN VERY IMPORTANT
CASES.TH
THE MEDIA COMES OUT AS A LOSER
IN THIS REPORT UNTIL THEY FIX
THOSE. A
>> Sean: WHAT ABOUT THE
MUELLER REPORT CONTAINING
DAMAGING INFORMATION ON ROD
ROSENSTEIN?
NOBODY REALLY HAS PICKED UP ON
THAT.
>> IF PEOPLE FLIP TO PAGE 11 ON
DERSHOWITZ'S NEW BOOK WILL
SEE THIS REALLY REMARKABLE
STATEMENT.
HE SAYS THE SCOPING MEMO GAVE
HIM THE ABILITY TO LOOK AT
CARTER PAGE'S CONTACTS WITH A
SENIOR RUSSIAN INTELLIGENCE
OFFICIALS AND THOSE NEVER
HAPPENED BUT WHERE DID THAT
INFORMATION COME FROM?
THE STEELE DOSSIER.
THAT MEANS A YEAR INTO THE
INVESTIGATION, THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT UNDER ROD ROSENSTEIN
EMPOWERED MUELLER BASED ON THE
DOCUMENT THAT WE NOW B KNOW WAS
FULL OF HOLES AND PROBABLY
ALMOST ENTIRELY FALSE.
PROBABLY A DIRTY TRICK BY THE
RUSSIANS ON THE AMERICAN PUBLIC.
THAT IS ONE OF THE MOST
ADMISSIONS IN THE REPORT.
HASN'T GOTTEN A LOT OF
ATTENTION.
I THINK ROD ROSENSTEIN HAS A
GOOD QUESTION TO ANSWER WHICH IS
WHY WOULD YOU USE THE DOSSIER
WHEN THE FBI KNEW AT THAT POINT
IT WASN'TSE ACCURATE?
>> Sean: PROFESSOR, I READ
YOUR COMMENTS ABOUT CNN.
I GUESS YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT THE
ATTORNEY, WHATEVER HIS NAME IS.
HERE'S THE IMPORTANT THING.
AVENATTI OR -- BUT HERE'S THE
IMPORTANT THING.
THERE ARE CIVIL LIBERTIES AT
STAKE.
WHERE ARE ALL THE PEOPLE ON THE
LEFT WHO USED TO CARE ABOUT
CIVIL LIBERTIES, BECAUSE THERE
WAS ONE AMERICAN, BECAUSE OF A
PHONY DOSSIER, THAT LOST HIS
CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHTS, AND THAT
DOSSIER WAS THE BULK OF
INFORMATION.
HE SAID NO DOSSIER, NO FISA
WARRANT.
THAT WAS NEVER VERIFIED BUT IT
WAS SIGNED OFF ON FOUR TIMES.
NOT ONLY A SPYING INSERT INTO
THE PRESIDENT'S CAMPAIGN, BUT
ALSO AMERICAN CITIZENS WERE HURA
HERE.
>> IT'S NOT ONLY ONE AMERICAN
WHO LOST HIS CIVIL LIBERTIES.
BECAUSE AN INVESTIGATION WAS
OPENED.
ALL AMERICANS HAVE THEIR CIVIL
LIBERTIES COMPROMISED.
WHEN YOU HAVE A DOSSIER
PRESENTED TO THE FISA COURT AND
PRESENTED AS THE WHOLE TRUTH,
WHEN THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
WITHHELD RELEVANT MATERIAL.
IF THEY CAN DO IT TO THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES,
THEY CAN DO IT TO ANY OF US, ANY
CITIZEN, AND WHEN YOU GET TO THE
ROSENSTEIN ISSUE, HE SURELY
SHOULD HAVE BEEN RECUSED FROM
THIS CASE AND WHEN YOU READ THE
REPORT, HIS ROLE IN THE FIRING
OF COMEY IS MINIMIZED.
HE IS INVOLVED IN BEING IN
CHARGE OF THE INVESTIGATION AND
YET HIS ROLE IS MINIMIZED
BECAUSE IF HE HAD PLAYED A
LARGER ROLE, THEN OBVIOUSLY HE
WOULD'VE HAD TO RECUSE HIMSELF
BECAUSE HE COULD HAVE BEEN A
POTENTIAL DEFENDANT OR A
POTENTIAL WITNESS IN THE CASE.
THE ENTIRE OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE DISCUSSION IS A C- LEGAL
DISCUSSION.
THE MUELLER REPORT GOT THE LAW
COMPLETELY WRONG.
THEY CAME TO THE CONCLUSION THAT
YOU COULD ACTUALLY INDICT A
PRESIDENT FOR EXERCISING HIS
CONSTITUTIONAL AUTHORITY.
THAT IS NOT THE LAW AND HAS
NEVER BEEN THE LAW AND IT NEVERH
SHOULD BE THE LAW AND EVERY
CIVIL LIBERTARIAN SHOULD BE
UPSET ABOUT THAT.
>> Sean: YOU DO AGREE WE HAVE
TO GET TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
>> YES.
>> Sean: IF WE DON'T, WHAT YOU
SPENT YOUR CAREER FIGHTING FOR
AND DEFENDING AND THE LAW YOU
HAVE BEEN TEACHING PREDICATED ON
THE GREATEST DOCUMENT GOD GAVE O
MAN,  THE CONSTITUTION, WE LOSE
IT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK THERE ARE
TWO INSTITUTIONS THAT ARE TO BE
LOOKING INTO IT.
FIRST IS THE INSPECTOR GENERAL.
I THINK HE IS A PERFECT PERSON
TO LOOK INTO IT BECAUSE IT TAKES
IT OUT OF PARTISANSHIP AND
SECOND, THE FISA COURT ITSELF
CAN APPOINT SOMEBODY TO LOOK AS
TO WHETHER OR NOT THERE WAS
CONTEMPT OF COURT COMMITTED BY
PEOPLE WHO MISLED THEM
DELIBERATELY.
YES, WE HAVETH TO GET TO THE
BOTTOM OF IT.
A NONPARTISAN WAY.
>> Sean: JOHN, LAST WORD.
>> THAT IS SPOT ON AND THAT IS
UNDERWAY.
WE HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY TO GET TO
THE BOTTOM OF THIS AND FIND THE
TRUTH.
>> Sean: THANK YOU, BOTH.
PROFESSOR, THANK YOU.
GREAT WORK THROUGHOUT ALL OF
THIS.>>
ON PEELING THE LAYERS OF THE
ONION.
SENATOR GRAHAM, NEWT GINGRICH,
PIERS MORGAN FIRED UP ON THIS■■■
BUSYGR NEWS WEEK.
TONIGHT ON "HANNITY."
♪ ♪
■C
These folks,
they don't have time to
go to the Post Office
They have businesses to grow
Customers to care for
Lives to get home to
They use Stamps.com
Print discounted postage
for any letter
Any package
Any time
Right from your computer
All the amazing services
of the Post Office
only cheaper
Get our Special TV Offer
A 4-week trial
plus postage and
a digital scale
Go to Stamps.com/tv and
never go to the Post Office
again!
♪ It is such a good time
to kiss ♪
to dance ♪
♪ It is such a good time to ♪
[ Laughing ]
♪ Scoobidoo doobidoo ♪
[ Goose honking ]
♪♪
[ Laughing ]
A bad day on the road still
beats a good one off it.
♪♪
Progressive helps keep you
out there.
♪ ♪
>> Sean: THE MUELLER REPORT
LAST WEEKEND
>> Sean:ST FOLLOWING THERE
RELEASE OF THE MOTHER REPORT,
QUESTIONS ARE RIGHTLY BEING
ASKED ABOUT WHAT COMES NEXT.
"MUELLER REPORT PUNKED THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL'S WORK.
CONGRESS WAS WRONG.
REPORT ANALYZES THE
CONSTITUTIONAL AUTHORITY TO
LEGISLATE AND IS NOT UPEND THE
SEPARATION OF POWERS BY CALLING
CONGRESS TO CONDUCT CONTINUE A
COMPLETED DOJ INVESTIGATION."
JOINING US NOW, THE FIRST
INTERVIEW SINCE THE MUELLER
REPORT CAME OUT.
SENATE JUDICIARY CHAIRMAN
LINDSEY GRAHAM.
WE KIND OF NEEDED YOU LAST WEEK
AND I DON'T KNOW WHERE YOU WERE.
WE COULD HAVE USED YOU.
LET'S GET YOUR GENERAL THOUGHTS
AND REACTIONS AND WHAT YOU WILL
DO.
>> NUMBER ONE, THE IDEA THAT THE
MUELLER REPORT IS NOT THE FINAL
WORD ON ALL THINGS TRUMP,
RUSSIAN COLLUSION, OBSTRUCTION.
IT IS NEWS TO ME.
I THOUGHT WE ALL TRUSTED
MUELLER.
HERE'S WHAT I THINK IS GOING ON
IN THE HOUSE.
THERE'S GOING TO BE A STAMPEDE
TO IMPEACH PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THEY WILL USE THE MUELLER REPORT
AND ANYTHING THEY CAN FIND TO
TRY TO DESTROY HIS PRESIDENCY.
NANCY PELOSI IS NOT IN CHARGE OF
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
THE RADICAL LEFT IS IN CHARGE.
I WILL EXPECT THERE WILL BELO
IMPEACHMENTRT PROCEEDINGS AND TE
MUELLER REPORT TO ME IS
VINDICATION OF PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> Sean: YOU SAID IT'S OVER
AND I AGREE WITH YOU.
>> IT'S OVER FOR ME.
>> Sean: LET ME TELL YOU, I
THINK WE HAVE HAD A NINE MONTHTE
INVESTIGATION BY THE FBI.
PETER STRZOK AND PAGE, THEY
SAID THERE IS NO THERE THERE.
THEN WE HAD THE HOUSE UNTIL
COMMITTEE INVESTIGATION AND THE
BIPARTISAN INVESTIGATION AND NOW
THE MUELLER REPORT.
YOU CAN'T STATE ANY MORE
CLEARLY, NO COLLUSION.
NOW THE AMERICAN PEOPLE, THE
ANSWER IS IN.
IF THEY WANT TO DO THIS ON TOP
OF THE GREEN DEAL, WHAT ARE THE
POLITICAL RAMIFICATIONS
FOR NOT SERVING THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE?
>> THEY WILL GET PUNISHED IN
202O AND I THINK PRESIDENT TRUMP
WILL GET REELECTED.
I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED IN '98 WHEN
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE UNDERSTOOD
WHAT THEY GOT WITH BILL CLINTON,
THEY UNDERSTAND PRESIDENT TRUMP
WARTS AND ALL.
MUELLER WAS THE GUY THAT I WAS
GOING TO LET LOOK AT, MAKE SURE
HE LOOKED AT THE IDEA AFTER
WORKING WITH THE RUSSIANS AND
THE VERDICT IS IN.
THERE WAS NO COLLUSION.
THERE WAS NO OBSTRUCTION OF A
CRIME THAT NEVER OCCURRED.
THE OBSTRUCTION THING WAS
BIZARRE TO ME TO BEGIN WITH.
HERE'S WHAT I THINK.
THEY WILL BE STAMPEDED TO
HIM SO MUCH AND I HATE IT FORTE
THE COUNTRY AND THE PRESIDENT
BUT IT WILL RESULT IN HIM M
GETTING REEL■O■O
THE MEDIAú/■/■/■/ NOT COVERING E
TRUMP PRESIDENCY, THEY ARE
TRYING TO DESTROY YET.
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY DOESN'T
ACCEPT THE FACT THAT HE WON SO
AT THE END OF THE DAY WE WILL
HAVE TO DEAL WITH THIS IN 2020
AT THE BALLOT BOX.
>> Sean: THERE ARE THREE BIG
COMPONENTS.
WE NOW KNOW THE INVESTIGATION
WITH HILARY WAS RIGGED.
LORETTA LYNCH WAS RUNNING EVERY
DECISION.
"A MATTER," NOT AN
INVESTIGATION.
THEN WE HAVE THE ATTEMPT TO USE
A PHONY RUSSIAN DOSSIER, EVEN
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" IS
ADMITTING THAT, WHICH IS
INTERESTING.
"THE WASHINGTON POST" WRITING
FOX NEWS WAS RIGHT, ESPECIALLY
HANNITY.
WHATEVER.
IT IS NOT ABOUT WHO WAS RIGHT
BUT A RIGGED INVESTIGATION AND
ATTEMPT TO BREAK A PRESIDENTIAL
ELECTION AND THEN ATTEMPT TO
UNSEAT A DULY ELECTED PRESIDENT.
WHAT WILL YOULD DO SPECIFICALLY?
>> THERE IS BEFORE AND AFTER THE
CAMPAIGN.
BEFORE THE CAMPAIGN I WANT TO
FIND OUT DID GEORGE PAPADOPOULOS
WAS HE WORKING WITH THE RUSSIANS
OR DID PLANT IN HIS MIND THAT
THE RUSSIANS HAD HILLARY
CLINTON'S EMAIL?
IN OTHER WORDS, DID THE
KNOWLEDGE ABOUT RUSSIA
AND THE CLINTON EMAILS COME FROM
SOMEBODY OTHER THAN RUSSIA?
HOW COULD YOU USE THE DOSSIER
FOUR DIFFERENT TIMES TO GET A
WARRANT AGAINST AN AMERICAN
CITIZEN WHEN IT'S GARBAGE?
WHY DIDN'T THEY TELL THE COURT
IT WAS A POLITICALLY MOTIVATED
DOCUMENT?
I WILL TRY TO FIND OUT ABOUT THE
COUNTERINTELLIGENCE
INVESTIGATION AND ABOUT HOW THE
FISA WARRANT WAS OBTAINED
AGAINST CARTER PAGE.
WAS THERE AN EFFORT TO INVOKE
THE 25TH AMENDMENT?
WAS TELLING THE TRUTH, McCABE
OR ROSENSTEIN?
THE PERSON WHO LEAKED
"THE WASHINGTON POST" SAID THAT
GENERAL FLYNN WAS BEING P
SURVEILLED DURING THE
TRANSITION, IF YOU CAN FIND OUTT
WHO THAT PERSON, THAT IS THE ONE
WHO STARTED ALL OF THIS.
>> Sean: IT MIGHT BE A LOT
EARLIER THAN THE DATE WE WEREE
TOLD, WHICH IS JULY 31ST.
DID OUR INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY
OUTSOURCE ILLEGAL ACTIVITIES TO
OUR ALLIES TO BYPASS AMERICAN
LAWS, INTEL ABUSE, TURNED ON
AMERICAN CITIZENS, UNMASKING,
LEAKING?
A LOT TO GET HERE.
LYING TO CONGRESS.
WE ARE ABOUT TO GET TO THIS.
GOOD TO SEE YOU AND WELCOME
BACK.
WHEN WE COME BACK, AN UPDATE ON
THE TERRIBLE TERROR ATTACK IN
SRI LANKA THAT LEFT NEARLY 300
DEAD INCLUDING AMERICANS
ON EASTER SUNDAY. T
NEWT GINGRICH AND ALSO
PIERS MORGAN IS ON FIRE.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHY.
♪ ♪
BUT I'M RELENTLESS TOO.
MBC DOESN'T TAKE A DAY
OFF, AND NEITHER WILL I.
AND I TREAT MY MBC WITH
EVERYDAY VERZENIO-
THE ONLY ONE OF ITS KIND
THAT CAN BE TAKEN EVERY DAY.
IN FACT, VERZENIO IS
A CDK4 & 6 INHIBITOR
FOR POSTMENOPAUSAL WOMEN
WITH HR+, HER2-
METASTATIC
BREAST CANCER,
APPROVED, WITH
HORMONAL THERAPY,
AS AN EVERYDAY
TREATMENT
FOR A RELENTLESS
DISEASE.
VERZENIO + AN AI IS
PROVEN TO HELP WOMEN
HAVE SIGNIFICANTLY MORE TIME
WITHOUT DISEASE PROGRESSION,
AND MORE THAN HALF OF WOMEN SAW
THEIR TUMORS SHRINK VS AN AI.
DIARRHEA
IS COMMON,
MAY BE SEVERE,
AND MAY CAUSE
DEHYDRATION
OR INFECTION.
BEFORE TAKING VERZENIO,
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU HAVE
FEVER, CHILLS, OR OTHER
SIGNS OF INFECTION.
VERZENIO MAY CAUSE LOW
WHITE BLOOD CELL COUNTS,
WHICH MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS INFECTION
THAT CAN LEAD TO DEATH.
SERIOUS LIVER
PROBLEMS CAN OCCUR.
SYMPTOMS MAY INCLUDE TIREDNESS,
LOSS OF APPETITE, STOMACH PAIN,
AND BLEEDING OR BRUISING
MORE EASILY THAN NORMAL.
BLOOD CLOTS THAT CAN LEAD
TO DEATH HAVE ALSO OCCURRED.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU NOTICE PAIN OR SWELLING
IN YOUR ARMS OR LEGS,
SHORTNESS OF BREATH, CHEST PAIN
OR RAPID BREATHING
OR HEART RATE.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU ARE
PREGNANT, BREASTFEEDING,
OR PLAN TO BECOME PREGNANT.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
INCLUDE NAUSEA, INFECTIONS,
LOW RED AND WHITE BLOOD
CELLS AND PLATELETS,
DECREASED APPETITE, HEADACHE,
ABDOMINAL PAIN, TIREDNESS,
VOMITING, AND HAIR
THINNING OR LOSS.
I'M RELENTLESS.
AND MY DOCTOR AND I CHOOSE TO
TREAT
MY METASTATIC
BREAST CANCER
WITH VERZENIO.
BE RELENTLESS.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
EVERYDAY VERZENIO.
j■■
♪ ♪
>> Sean: WITH 290n:■a PEO
ED INCLUDING AMERICANS, MORE
THAN 400 INJURED, AFTER A
RADICAL ISLAMIC TERROR GROUP
■  ■@■@■ERS TO
DETONATE EXPLOSIVES TO HOTELS
AND CHURCHES
ON E EASTER SUNDAY IN SRI LANKA.
THIS COMES AS ATTACKS AGAINST
CHRISTIANS ARE SPIKING.
2018, OVER 4,000 CHRISTIANS
KILLED FOR FAITH-RELATED
REASONS.
HERE WITH REACTION WHO WROTE THE
NEW FICTION NOVEL, TITLED
"COLLUSION", OUT NEXT
TUESDAY AND AVAILABLE FOR
PREORDER ON Amazon.com.
THE FORMER SPEAKER OF THE HOUSE,
FOX NEWS CONTRIBUTOR
NEWT GINGRICH.
I'M SURE IT DOESN'T AT ALL
REFLECT REAL LIFE EVENTS AT ALL.
>> IT INVOLVES REAL COLLUSION
BETWEEN A SENATE STAFF MEMBER
AND SOME RUSSIANS WANT TO POISON
THE SENATE.
IT IS REAL COLLUSION.
IT'S NOT SOME PHONY DEAL.
>> Sean: WHAT DO YOU THINK OF
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" EVEN
ACKNOWLEDGING NOW THAT THEY
MIGHT HAVE BEEN A DISINFORMATION
CAMPAIGN, THE DOSSIER, FROM THE
VERY BEGINNING?
GUYS LIKE BOB WOODWARD, WELCOME
TO THE PARTY.
THE STEELE DOSSIER BOUGHT AND
PAID FOR BY CLINTON, YOU HAVE TO
EXAMINE IT FURTHER.
WHERE HAVE THEY BEEN FOR TWO
YEARS?
>> I THINK THERE WAS A PICTURE
THAT HAD BEEN PAINTED THAT MADE
A LOT OF PEOPLE WHO HATED TRUMP
FEEL GOOD AND THEY HAD ENORMOUS
HOPE THAT THAT PICTURE WAS GOING
TO TURN OUT TO BE REALITY.
IT WAS A SOCIAL MOVEMENT.
THE SORT OF THING YOU SAW THE
MIDDLE AGES WHERE PEOPLE WOULD
GET SWEPT UP, THE SALEM
WITCHCRAFT TRIALS WERE VERY
SIMILAR.
A MASS HYSTERIA AND ALL OF THESE
SUPPOSEDLY SOPHISTICATED PEOPLE
GO RUNNING DOWN THE ROAD WHILE
CHANTING THE SAME THINGS.
I THINK THIS IS THE BEGINNING OF
WHAT I HOPE WILL BE A MUCH
LONGER AND TOUGHER
SELF-EVALUATION THAN JUST
SAYING, IS IT OVER OR NOT OVER?
>> Sean: MR. SPEAKER, HELL
WILL FREEZE OVER.
IS NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
LINDSEY GRAHAM ACTUALLY SAID THE
WORDS THAT THEY ARE RUSHING OR
STAMPEDING TO IMPEACH.
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT?
WHEN YOU COUPLE THIS NEVER
ENDING, NONSTOP, USE THE IRS
EVEN TO DESTROY TRUMP PSYCHOSIS
WITH THE NEW GREEN DEAL, NO OIL
OR GAS, RETROFIT EVERY BUILDING.
NO COMBUSTION ENGINE, PLANES,
COWS, EVERYTHING IS FREE, HOW
DOES THIS PLAY A POLITICALLY?
>> I THINK HE JUST BROUGHT
TOGETHER THREE OR FOUR DIFFERENT
STREAMS.
IF YOU START OUT WITH THE NOTION
THAT OCASIO-CORTEZ
AND HER ALLIES ARE CRAZY, YOU
HAVE TO DECIDE HOW MANY
AMERICANS ARE GOING TO BUY THAT.
HISTORICALLY IT IS NOT VERY
MANY.
THEY GET BIG COVERAGE IN THE
NEWS MEDIA AND THEY LOOK LIKE
THEY ARE OUT OF TOUCH WITH
REALITY.
IF YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT THE
DEMOCRATIC NOMINEE FOR
PRESIDENT, THEY HAVE A HUGE
KIPROBLEM.
THEY VERY LIKELY WILL
GET SANDERS.
WE'LL HAVE A STRAIGHT UP FIGHT.
IF YOU THINK SOCIALISM WORKS, IF
YOU LOVE VENEZUELA, YOU ALWAYS
WANTED TO BE IN ZIMBABWE AND YOU
THINK CUBA IS THE FUTURE,
YOU WILL HAVE A CANDIDATE.
IF YOU LIKE THE BEST ECONOMY IN
MODERN TIMES, THE LOWEST BLACK
UNEMPLOYMENT, THE LOWEST LATINO
EMPLOYMENT, YOU HAVE A
DIFFERENT PARTY LED BY
DONALD TRUMP.
THAT IS A BIG PIECE OF THIS.
I DON'T WANT TO GET OFF OF THIS
FOR A SECOND.
TWO BIG TOPICS VERY QUICKLY.
THERE IS A WAR AGAINST
CHRISTIANITY.
WE HAVE TO BE CLEAR WITH THAT AS
THERE IS A WAR AGAINST SEMITISM.
IF YOU LOOK AT ANTI-SEMITIC
ACTIONS, IN FRANCE, 4,000
ANTI-SEMITIC ACTS LAST YEAR.
PEOPLE ARE FOCUSING ON
IF YOU LOOK AT THE NUMBER OF
CHURCHES BURNING DOWN,
PEOPLE ARE FOCUSING ON
NOTRE DAME BECAUSE IT IS SO BIG
BUT THERE ARE A LOT OF OTHER
CHURCHES BEINGLE VANDALIZED IN
FRANCE.'L'L■p■@■p■p■@■LNG KILD
NEITHER P OBAMA NOR■÷■÷
SECRETARY CLINTON COULD DESCRI
THEM AS CHRISTIANS.
SOMEHOW THEY BOTH IN PARALLEL
CAME UP WI "EASTER
WORSHIPERS."
YOU HAVE T, HOW COULD
EY BOTH COME UP WITH THE SAMEAV■
TERM ON THE SAME WEEKEND?■
THAT IS AN EXAMPLE, IT IS SO
HARD FOR THEM TO COME TO GRIPS I
WITH, THIS IS A WAR AGAINST
CHRISTIANITY.
JUST AS IT IS A WAR AGAINST
JUDAISM.S
WE OUGHT TO BE CLEAR.
WE NEED THE INTELLECTUAL AND
MENTAL TOUGHNESS TO SAYWE THIS.
I WANT TO JUMP BOUR
OTHER TOPIC.
A SINGLE EXAMPLE.
I'M HOPING THAT SENATOR GRAHAM
WILL ASSIGN SOMEBODY ON HIS
STAFF TO GO TO THE 500 PEOPLE,
500, WHO HAD TO DEAL WITH
MUELLER AND ASK THEM, WHAT WERE
THEIR LEGAL FEES?
THIS MAY WELL HAVE COST A HALF
BILLION DOLLARS TO CITIZENS
WHO WERE TOTALLY INNOCENT.
THAT OUGHT TO RAISE SOME VERY
SERIOUS FUNDAMENTAL QUESTIONS
ABOUT HOW THIS WHOLE SYSTEM IS
NOW WORKING.
FRANKLY IT IS CORRUPT.
IT IS AN ABUSE OF POWER AND IF
YOU WATCH WHAT IS GOING ON AND
LOOK AT PEOPLE PUT AWAY IN
SOLITARYRY CONFINEMENT.
THERE WAS A WOMAN WHO WAS IN C
SOLITARY CONFINEMENT FOR
THTWO-THIRDS OF A
POTENTIAL TERM. W
THAT WAS BEFORE SHE WAS
CONVICTED OF ANYTHING.
THAT IS NOT AMERICA.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD LET UP
ON THIS.
WE SHOULD LOOK VERY CLEARLY AT
THE REPORT AND ASK A SIMPLE
QUESTION FOR BOB MUELLER.
WHEN DID HE FIGURE OUT THAT
THERE WAS NOTHING THERE?
EVERY DAY AFTER THAT THAT HE
ALLOWED THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES TO BE UNDER A
CLOUD OF SUSPICION, HE DID A
DISSERVICE WHICH WEAKENED THE
UNITED STATES.
IT DIDN'T WEAKEN DONALD TRUMP.
>> Sean: HOW DID HE NOT LOOK
INTO THE RUSSIAN DOSSIER?
>> I THINK IT WILL BE HEALTHY
FOR PEOPLE TO ASK HIM QUESTIONS
ABOUT THE DECISION POINTS AND
THE ONE SIDEDNESS AND FRANKLY I
THINK YOU HAVE TO GO BACK AND
LOOK AT CLINTON AND THEIR F
RELATIONSHIP WITH THE RUSSIANS.
IF THERE IS ANY MONEY
RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN THE
RUSSIANS AND AMERICAN
POLITICIANS, IT IS BILL AND
HILLARY CLINTON, NOT
DONALD TRUMP.
I DON'T THINK THIS WILL GO AWAY.
THIS IS PART OF SOMETHING WE
HAVE TO DIG INTO.
>> Sean: IT CAN'T.
IF WE DON'T GET TO THE BOTTOM OF
IT -- THIS IS THE BIGGEST ABUSE
OFAB POWER POWER SCANDAL,
CORRUPTION
IF THIS HAPPENS AND WE DON'T
HOLD PEOPLE ACCOUNTABLE IT WILL
ONLY HAPPEN AGAIN AND AGAIN.
WE LOVE WHEN YOU'RE BACK IN THE
STATES.
I KNOW YOU ARE HAPPY AT THE
P P AVATICAN.BC
I CAN'T BOOK YOU AT 2:00 IN THE
MORNING.
IT IS A LITTLE DIFFICULT.
>> I AM HERE.
>> Sean: OH, TODAY I AM HERE.
>> [LAUGHS]
>> Sean: WHEN WE COME BACK,
JUSSIE SMOLLETT'S BROTHER WROTE
AN OP-ED BELIEVING HIS BROTHER,
AND YOU WON'T BELIEVE WHAT IT
SAID.
TRACE GALLAGHER HAS THAT REPORT
AND PIERS MORGAN HAS BEEN ON
FIRE.
■■■■■■■■■÷■■l■WHY STRAIGHT
AHEAD.
♪ ♪
■■
-Meg! There you are. Did you
take a picture of the cake
to put on our website?
I mean I would have
but I'm a commercial vehicle
so I don't have hands...
or a camera...or a website.
Should we franchise?
Is the market ready for that?
Can we franchise?
How do you do that? Meg! Oh Meg!
We should do that thing
where you put the business cards
in the fishbowl
and somebody wins something.
-Meg: Hi. I'm here for...
I'm here for the Evans' wedding.
-We've got the cake in the back,
so, yeah.
-Meg: Thank you.
-Progressive knows small
business makes big demands.
-You're not gonna make it,
you're not gonna make it!
As we can do
her next wedding too!
-So we'll design
the insurance solution
that fits your business.
These folks,
they don't have time to
go to the Post Office
They have businesses to grow
Customers to care for
Lives to get home to
They use Stamps.com
Print discounted postage
for any letter
Any packageamps.com
Any time
Right from your computer
All the amazing services
of the Post Office
only cheaper
Get our Special TV Offer
A 4-week trial
plus postage and
a digital scale
Go to Stamps.com/tv and
never go to the Post Office
again!
Is this ride safe?
I assembled it myself last
night.
I think I did an OK job.
Just OK?
What if something bad happens?
We just move to the next town.
Just OK is not OK.
Espeomes to your
networ■
AT&T is America's best wireless
network
according to America's biggest
test. Now with 5G Evolution.
The First Step to 5G.
More for your thing. That's our
thing.
♪ ♪
>> Sean: THE JUSSIE SMOLLETT
HATE CRIME HOAX SAGA IS TAKING
AN INTERESTING TURN THIS EVENING
AFTER "EMPIRE"'S BROTHER WROTE
AN OP-ED THIS WEEKEND.
LIVE FROM OUR WEST COAST
NEWSROOM, FOX NEWS CORRESPONDENT
TRACE GALLAGHER.
IT'S GETTING INTERESTING.
>> INDEED, IT IS.
>> IN THE ESSAY HE WROTE FOR
BET, HE H SAYS HIS YOUNGER BROTR
"IN LESS THAN THREE MONTHS HIS
LIFE HAS BEEN TURNED UPSIDE DOWN
AS MY FAMILY AND I HAVE
WITNESSED HIM ENDURE UNRELENTING
ATTACKS TO HIS CHARACTER AND
REPUTATION."
HE GOES ON TO SAY JUSSIE HE IS
EXPERIENCING POST TRAUMA AND
NIGHT TERRORS ANDOS THE BROTHER
BLAMES THE CHICAGO POLICE
DEPARTMENT FOR LEAKING
INFORMATION.
"WHAT CONCERNED ME THE MOST AS
THE CHICAGO POLICE DEPARTMENT
CONTINUED THEIR CAMPAIGN AGAINST
JUSSIE, I NOTICED AN ONLINE
BANDWAGON APPROACHING,
IGNORING WHETHER THERE WERE ANY
REAL FACTS TO SUGGEST HIS
GUILT."
BUT AS COOK COUNTY PROSECUTORS
POINTED OUT, THERE ARE CERTAINLY
INCRIMINATING■  FACTS, LIKE
SMOLLETT S HIS ALLEGED
ATTACKERS WERE WHITE SKINNED,
WHEN IN FACT THEY WERE BLACK
BROTHERS, WHO HE KNEW ANDBR
ALLEGEDLY PAID TO HELP HIM
ORCHESTRATE THE PONY ATTACK,
INCLUDING GIVING THEM MONEY TO
BUY A ROPE, SKI MASKS, GASOLINE,
GLOVES, AND RED CAPS THAT
RESEMBLE MAKE AMERICA GREAT
AGAIN HATS.
HE ALSO ASKED WHAT IF JUSSIE IS
TELLING THE TRUTH?
EVEN PROSECUTORS WHO DROPPED THE
CHARGES SAY, HE IS NOT TELLING
THE TRUTH.
SEAN?
>> Sean: TRACE GALLAGHER WITH
THE REPORT.
JOINING ME NOW, DailyMail.com,
HAS
BECOME A FRIEND OF MINE AND HE
WAS ONCE A COMPETITOR.
I NEVER DISLIKED HIM THEN EXCEPT
FOR THE SECOND AMENDMENT.
WE WILL DEBATE THAT ONE DAY.
>>XC [LAUGHS]
>> Sean: I HAVE COME TO ADMIRE
YOUR FIGHT, YOUR WIT, YOURD
HUMOR.
YOU ARE VERY IMPRESSIVE AND I
READ YOUR STUFF ALL THE TIME.
LIBERALS SCREAMING TO IMPEACH
TRUMP, YOU HAD A --
YOU WERE ON FIRE.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME AND I
WANT TO OFFER MY DEEPEST
SYMPATHY TO JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
IT MUST BE AWFUL TO HAVE
POST-TRAUMATIC STRESS DISORDER
FROM SOMETHING THAT YOU FAKED
YOURSELF.
THE POOR GUY.
OUR HEARTS GO OUT TO HIM.
ALL THOSE NIGHTMARES ABOUT DID I
OR DID I NOT GIVE THEM THE RIGHT
AMOUNT OF MONEY IN THE CHECK IJO
THIS ATTACK?
DO ME A FAVOR.
THAT GOT ME ANGRY.
LET'S TURN TO THIS ISSUE OF THE
REPORT.
THERE ARE 400 PAGES BUT WHAT
WAS THE REPORT TO SET UP TO BE?
THE REPORT WAS AT A VERY CLEARLY
TO INVESTIGATE.
MUELLER WAS TO INVESTIGATE
WHETHER THERE WAS A CONSPIRACY
BY DONALD TRUMP OR HIS CAMPAIGNN
TEAM WITH THE RUSSIANS TORE
BASICALLY FIX THE ELECTION.
I CAN'T IMAGINE A MORE SERIOUS
CHARGE AGAINST ANY SERVING
PRESIDENT.
THEY BETRAYED THEIR COUNTRY WITH
A FOREIGN ENEMY TO FIX A U.S.
ELECTION AND FOR TWO YEARS THE
MEDIA IN THIS COUNTRY AND THE
DEMOCRATS AND SCREAMING LIBERAL
CELEBRITIES LIKE JUSSIE SMOLLETT
WHO LED THE CHARGE ON THIS, HAVE
SCREAMED COLLUSION, COLLUSION!
THIS WAS A DONE DEAL.
MUELLER WAS THE SAVIOR, THE MAN
ON THE WHITE HORSE RIDING INTO
TOWN TO TAKE DOWNHE PRESIDENT
TRUMP ON COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA
AND HE WOULD BE EXPOSED AS A
TRAITOR AND THIS WOULD BE THE
END OF HIS PRESIDENCY.
THE MUELLER REPORT COMES OUT AND
IT TURNS OUT IT WAS ALL
NONSENSE.
IT WAS TO QUOTE DONALD TRUMP,
"FAKE NEWS."
I TURNED THE DAY AFTER THE FULL
REPORT WAS PUBLISHED AND LOOKED
AT THE PAPERS,
"THE WASHINGTON POST" AND
"THE NEW YORK TIMES," WHO BOTH
WON PULITZER PRIZES FOR THEIR
COVERAGE OF RUSSIA COLLUSION AND
NEITHER OF THEM
REMEMBERED TO MENTION IN THEIR
BANNER HEADLINES THE DAY AFTER
THE FULL PUBLICATION OF THE FULL
REPORT, NEITHER REMEMBERED TO
MENTION THAT THE CONCLUSION BY
MUELLER WAS THAT THERE WAS NO
COLLUSION.
INSTEAD THEY WENT FOR MORE TRUMP
BASHING.
I TURNED TO CABLE NEWS, SOME OF
YOUR RIVALS.
SOME I USED TO WORK AT.
THEY, TOO, MOVED VERY SWIFTLY
FROM COLLUSION THAT THEY HAD
BEEN SCREAMING ABOUT FOR TWO
YEARS TO NOW OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE.
LET'S ANALYZE THAT FOR A COUPLE
OF SECONDS.
WE ARE SUPPOSED TO BELIEVE THAT
DONALD TRUMP COMMITTED REPEATED
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICECE OVER A
CRIME THAT HE NOW, AS WE ALL
KNOW, DID NOT COMMIT?
HE IS TRYING TO OBSTRUCT PEOPLE
FROM INVESTIGATING SOMETHING HE
SAYS HE DIDN'T DO AND THE T
SPECIAL COUNSEL HAS CONFIRMED HE
DIDN'T DO.
IT IS RIDICULOUS, IT IS A FARCE,
IT IS MAKING A MOCKERY OF
AMERICA IN THE SAME WAY THAT
BACK IN MY COUNTRY OVER BREXIT
WITH OUR DEPARTURE FROM THE
EUROPEAN UNION.
THE PEOPLE WHO LOST THE VOTE
REMAINED AND I WAS ONE OF THEM
WHO REFUSED TO ACCEPT THE
RESULTS.
DO NOT WANT THE COUNTRY TO
BREXIT.
THE LIBERALS HERE ARE REFUSING
TO ACCEPT RESULTS IN 2016.
HILLARY WON THE POPULAR VOTE.
WHO CARES?
IT'S NOT ABOUT THE POPULAR VOTE.
NOW THEY REFUSE TO ACCEPT THE
RESULTS OF THE MUELLER REPORT.
THE ONE THAT THEY SAID WOULD BE
ABSOLUTELY THE FINAL PIECE.
IT IS A DISGRACE!
>> Sean: THAT WAS SO WELL
DONE.
I CAN'T TOP THAT.
YOU ARE EDGY.
"THE DAILY MAIL" IS EDGY.
THIS ISN'T EDGY.
THIS IS AN OUTRIGHT LIE,
CONSPIRACY THEORIES BASED ON
MOSTLY ANONYMOUS SOURCES.
WHAT IS THE FALLOUT?
I
DON'T THINK THEY EVER GET
RID OF THE FAKE NEWS BRANDING OF
DONALD TRUMP.
>> I'M ACTUALLY STAGGERED WITH
CNN, WHERE USED TO WORK, WHERE
USED TO WORK, I HAVE GREAT
FRIENDS THERE.
THEY HAVE GONE COMPLETELY IN THE
TANK ANTI-TRUMP.
I DON'T KNOW WHY THEY HAVE DONE
THAT OTHER THAN IT GIVES THEM A
LOT OF MONEY I GUESS.
IT DAMAGES THE CREDIBILITY AND I
WISH THEY WEREN'T DOING IT.
I WISH THAT SOMEWHERE IN AMERICA
IT WOULD GO BACK TO REPRESENTING
TRUMP IN A FAIR WAY.
YOU CAN ACTUALLY SAY LOOK, THE
MUELLER REPORT CAME BACK AND
SAID NO COLLUSION.
END, PERIOD, MOVE ON.
THE DEMOCRATS, FUELED BY THE
MEDIA, TRY TO CONTINUE TO FIGHT
THIS, I'M TELLING YOU WHAT
WILL HAPPEN, DONALD TRUMP WILL
GET REELECTED AND HE WILL HAVE
FOUR MORE YEARS OF THE THIS.
>> Sean: AMAZING ANALYSIS.
WE HOPE YOU COME BACK MORE
OFTEN.
PIERS MORGAN, THANK YOU.
WHEN WE COME BACK, LAWRENCE
JONES BACK TO
SAN FRANCISCO.
HE WILL SEE HOW THAT LIBERAL
CITY IS
DEALING WITH THE HUMAN FECES AND
THE NEEDLE CRISIS ALL OVER THE
PLACE.
A SNEAK PREVIEW OF TOMORROW'S
REPORT.
YOU WANT TO SEE THIS.
♪ ♪
♪♪
>> LAST WEEK WE TOLD YOU ABOUT
HUMAN FECES IN A CRISIS IN
SAN FRANCISCO AND NEEDLES.
WE SENT LAWRENCE JONES TO
CALIFORNIA TO CHECK OUT IT.
THE FULL REPORT WILL AIR
TOMORROW.
HERE'S A SNEAK PREVIEW.
>> THERE'S FECES EVERYWHERE,
HOMELESS PEOPLE, NEEDLES.
IS THAT THE NORM AROUND HERE?
>> UNFORTUNATELY IT IS.
THE CITY HAS BECOME SO MUCH
WORSE IN THE LAST TEN YEARS.
>> EVERYBODY IS SHOOTING UP UP
THE STREET.
THEY DON'T CARE.
SELLING DOPE, CRACK.
WHATEVER.
>> IT'S A BAD SITUATION.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE SOLUTION
WILL BE.
>> PEOPLE SHOOT UP IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE STREET.
>> WHILE THE KIDS ARE CROSSING.
FAMILIES --
>> EVERYTHING.
>> WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU THOSE