THE STREET.
THEY DON'T CARE.
SELLING DOPE, CRACK.
WHATEVER.
>> IT'S A BAD SITUATION.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE SOLUTION
WILL BE.
>> PEOPLE SHOOT UP IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE STREET.
>> WHILE THE KIDS ARE CROSSING.
FAMILIES --
>> EVERYTHING.
>> WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU THOSE
PICTURES TOMORROW.
THAT'S ALL THE TIME WE HAVE
LEFT.
WE WILL NEVER BE PART OF THE
HATE MEDIA.
AND CONGRESSMAN, WELCOME BACKS,
FILLING IN FOR LAURA.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HAVE A GOOD SHOW.
>> I'M JASON CHAFFETZ IN FOR
LAURA INGRAHAM.
TONIGHT, THE BIGGEST REVELATION
IN THE MUELLER REPORT NOBODY IS
TALKING ABOUT.
HOW THE OBAMA TEAM WAS ASLEEP AT
THE WHEEL WHILE RUSSIA WAS ON
THE ATTACK.
AND WHY DID PRESIDENT OBAMA AND
SECRETARY HILLARY CLINTON IGNORE
THE TRUTH ABOUT THE ATTACK ON
CHRISTIANITY?
VICTOR DAVID HANSON HERE IN
MOMENTS.
MEXICAN TROOPS PULL THEIR
WEAPONS ON U.S. SOLDIERS ON OUR
SIDE OF THE BORDER?
WHAT SHOULD OUR RESPONSE BE?
THAT REPORT AHEAD.
A HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT SAYS HE
WAS EXPELLED FROM SCHOOL FOR
BEING A CONSERVATIVE.
THE "THE INGRAHAM ANGLE"
OBTAINED SECRET AUDIO RECORDINGS
THAT BACK UP HIS
FIRST, HOURS AGO, SPEAKER NANCY
PELOSI AND HER LEADERSHIP TEAM
TOLD DEMOCRATIC MEMBERS THAT
THEY WON'T BE MOVING FORWARD
WITH IMPEACHMENT.
HOW MUCH LONGER CAN SHE HOLD
OUT?
WHAT THE BIG NAMES IN HER PARTY
ARE DEMANDING HAPPEN RIGHT NOW.
>> THERE'S ENOUGH INFORMATION
THERE, NOT ONLY ON OBSTRUCTION
OF JUSTICE BUT ALSO ON COLLUSION
OR CONSPIRACY.
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO CALL IT, TO
MOVE FORWARD WITH IMPEACHMENT ON
THIS PRESIDENT.
>> THE CONTUSION SAYS THE
PRESIDENT ENGAGES IN THIS KIND
OFspspspspspspACTIVITY,spspspspp
>> YOU THINK THIS IS?p
IMPEACHABLE?
>> YEAH, I DO.
>> EARLIER TODAY, THE LAST MAN
YOU SAW THERE, JERRY NADLER, THE
HOUSE JUDICIARY SUBPOENAED DON
McGAHN.
WHILE PELOSI IS NOT CALLING FOR
AN IMMEDIATE IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDING, SHE'S LETTING THE
CHAIRMAN OF THE JUDICIARY OFF
THE LEAD.
PRESIDENT TRUMP BUSHED OFF THE
EFFORTS.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT, MR. PRESIDENT?
>> JOINING ME IS DAN BONGINO
A FOX NEWS CONTRIBUTOR AND OFF
OF "EXONERATED" AND CHRIS HAHN,
HOST OF "THE AGGRESSIVE
PROGRESSIVE" PODCAST.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
YOU'RE ON FOX NEWS FREQUENTLY.
CHRIS, CAN YOU ADMIT OUT LOUD
THERE WAS NO COLLUSION?
CAN YOU SAY THAT OUT LOUD?
>> WELL, THE MUELLER REPORT SAYS
THERE'S NO COLLUSION.
I SAID I WOULD TRUST THE MUELLER
REPORT.
I READ THE COLLUSION SECTION.
IT APPEARS WHILE THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN WAS HAPPY TO GETTING
THIS REPORT FROM RUSSIA, THEY
DIDN'T FORM A CRIMINAL
CONSPIRACY WITH THAT, SO THAT
PART OF THE INVESTIGATION IS
SETTLED THAT DOESN'T MEAN WE
SHOULD HEAR ABOUT WHAT IS GOING
ON IN PUBLIC THROUGH TESTIMONY.
BUT THE OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE
PORTION, THAT IS VERY TROUBLING.
I REMEMBER WHEN THERE THERE WAS
A YOUNG FORMER PLACE KICKER FROM
UTAH SITTING IN THE CHAIRS OF
ONE OF THOSE COMMITTEES.
HE WOULD HAVE INVESTIGATED THIS
FULLY.
SO I EXPECT THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES TODAY IS GOING
TO HAVE HEARINGS AND GET THE
WITNESSES THAT MUELLER
INVESTIGATED TO TESTIFY IN
PUBLIC SO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
CAN SEE WHAT HAPPENED.
BUT THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE
THE TRUTH.
>> CHRIS, YOU KNOW WHAT IT'S
LIKE TO HAVE IF GOAL POSTS MOVED
ON YOU.
THAT'S WHAT THE DEMOCRATS ARE
TRYING TO DO, MOVE THE GOAL
POSTS.
THEY BARKED ABOUT COLLUSION FOR
TWO YEARS AND NOW IT DOESN'T
HAPPEN.
CHRIS IS WILLING TO ADMIT THAT
IT'S NOT THERE.
>> YEAH, BUT I FIND IT FUNNY HOW
CHRIS THROWS IN THIS SNIDE
REMARK THAT THEY WERE SO H TAKOA
THEY DIDN'T GET ANY INFORMATION
FROM RUSSIA.
THEY SHOWED@  UP TO TALK ABOUT
ADOPTION.
SECONDLY, THE ONLY CAMPAIGN THAT
WE ABSOLUTELY KNOW TOOK
INFORMATIO RUS IS
HILLARY CLINTON.
BUT CHRIS LEAVES T@ @  PART OUT.
AWFULLY CONVENIENT.
IT'S LIKE DEM AMNE
SECONDLY, THE OBSTRUCTION CASE
IS GOING TO BE BIGGEST
BOOMERANG SINCE EDDIE MURPHY'S
BUILDING.
JASON, DON'T FORGET THIS.
YOU KNOW THIS BETTER THAN
ANYONE.
THE WAY YOU GUYS IN CONGRESS
FOUND OUT ABOUT ALL OF THE FBI
MALFEASANCE IN THE TRUMP CASE IS
BECAUSE THE DEMOCRATS COMPLAINED
ABOUT THE HANDLING OF THE
HILLARY CLINTON E-MAIL
INVESTIGATION.
SO --
>> I'LL TELL YOU WHAT --
>> SO CHRIS, HOLD ON.
NOBODY INTERRUPT ME.
LET ME TALK.
I DON'T INTERRUPT YOU EVER.
LET THE DEMOCRATS KEEP OPENING
UP THIS BOX.
PLEASE.
BECAUSE ONCE WE GET TO THE
BOTTOM OF THIS, IT'S GOING TO BE
UGLY.
>> CHRIS, I WANT YOU TO RESPOND.
BUT CHRIS, IN ADDITION TO WHAT
DAN JUST SAID, I WANT YOU TO
HEAR WHAT ADAM SCHIFF SAID.
GO AHEAD.
>> THE OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE IN
PARTICULAR IN THIS CASE IS FAR
WORSE THAN ANYTHING THAT RICHARD
NIXON DID.
THE BREAK-IN BY THE RUSSIANS OF
THE DEMOCRATIC INSTITUTIONS,
FOREIGN ADVERSARY, FAR MORE
SIGNIFICANT THAN THE PLUMBERS
BREAKING INTO THE DEMOCRATIC
HEADQUARTERS.
SO YES, THIS IS MORE SIGNIFICANT
THAN WATERGATE.
>> HE MAKES THAT CLAIM AS IF
DONALD TRUMP DIRECTED THE
RUSSIANS TO DO IT, WHICH IS
TOTALLY FALSE AND MISLEADING,
CHRIS.
>> I WANT TO MAKE DAN A DEAL AND
YOU, JASON.
I'LL BE HAPPY TO FIND OUT IF
THERE'S ANY REAL SPYGATE GOING
ON AS LONG AS WE DON'T BLOCK
SUBPOENAS TO GET McGAHN IN TO
FIND OUT IF ANY REAL OBSTRUCTION
OF JUSTICE HAPPENED HERE, WHICH
I THINK DID.
SO I'M HAPPY TO HEAR IT.
I THINK ADAM SCHIFF IS OVER THE
TOP THERE SAYING THIS IS WATERS
THAN WATERGATE.
THE OBSTRUCTION PORTION MAKES IT
WORSE THAN ANYTHING BILL CLINTON
WAS IMPEACHED FOR.
I THINK THE AMERICAN PEOPLE NEED
TO UNDERSTAND AND THE CHAOS
INSIDE THAT WHITE HOUSE THE LAST
TWO YEARS.
ONCE THAT TRUTH GETS OUT, THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE CAN JUDGE FOR
THEMSELVES WHAT THEY SHOULD DO
WITH THE PRESIDENT.
>> THE SPECIAL PROSECUTOR WROTE
HUNDREDS OF PAGES ABOUT THIS.
I DOUBT THAT ADAM SCHIFF OR
JERRY NADLER, ANY OF THESE OTHER
PEOPLE CAN COME UP WITH
ANYTHING.
IF THEY HAD SOMETHING --
>> I THINK HE DID PUT A PAGE
TOGETHER.
I READ THE RECORD.
HE PUT A PAGE KEPT AND LEFT IT
FOR CONGRESS TO BE THE JUDGE.
THE OLC MEMO HAS NOT --
>> THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
ADDRESSED THAT.
IT'S NOT TRUE.
I HAVE TO GO.
ONE OTHER THING.
I WANT TO GO TO ONE OTHER THING.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S OTHER PARTS OF
THIS.
YOU HAVE ELIJAH CUMMINGS THAT IS
PUT FORWARD A DOCUMENT THAT HE
WANTS OUT THERE.
THE TRUMP TEAM ACTUALLY SUED TO
MAKE SURE THAT THAT DOESN'T
HAPPEN.
DAN,S THE RIGHT MOVE BY
THE PRESIDENT?
>> YOU MEAN THEY'RE LOOKING FOR
HIS FIN■ú NOW?
>> YEAH.
DIGGING FOR ANYTHING.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT THE PRESIDENT
SHOULD DO?
I'M SERIOUS.
THE PRESIDENT SHOULD FLIP A
DOUBLE BARREL MIDDLE FINGER TO
DEMOCRATS AND SAY I'M A BUSINESS
GUY.
I GOT ELECTED PRESIDENT.
I DON'T OWE YOU JACK SQUAT ON MY
TAX RETURNS.
WHY DOES THE PRESIDENT HAVE ANY
OBLIGATION WHATSOEVER TO SHOW A
BUNCH OF POLITICAL HACKS WHO
HAVE LIED ABOUT HIM FOR THREE
YEARS NOW, FABRICATING ABSURD
STORIES ABOUT COLLUSION,
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE,
FELONIOUS MOPERY.
THEY MADE THIS UP.
NOW THEY WANT HIS TAX RETURNS
AND WE'RE SUPPOSED TO GO YEAH,
NO PROBLEM, FELLOWS.
YOU'RE SUCH BEACONS OF MORAL
AUTHORITY.
HE SHOULD TELL THEM TO POUND
SAND.
I WOULD.
>> I WISH I HAD MORE TIME.
NOT ONLY TRYING TO GET THE TAX
RETURNS BUT HIS FINANCIAL
RECORDS FOR HIS KIDS AND
BUSINESSES.
THERE'S NO FINANCIAL --
THERE'S --
>> JASON --
>> GENTLEMEAVE TO MOVE ON.
I WISH I COULD DO AN HOUR WITH
YOU, CHRIS.
I THINK YOU'RE SMART ON THIS
STUFF BUT YOU'RE SO TOTALLY
WRONG.
I HAVE TO THANK BOTH OF YOU.
>> IF THE PRESIDENT WANTS US TO
KNOW HOW RICH HE IS, HE SHOULD
SHOW US HIS TAX RETURNS.
>> HE DOESN'T YOU THAT.
>> HAVE TO GO.
VERY DEEP IN THE MUELLER REPORT
ARE A NUMBER OF PASSAGES THAT
PAINT A STORY OF A OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION THAT WAS TOTALLY
UNPREPARED FOR THE THREAT OF
RUSSIA.
FOR MORE, WE GO TO CATHERINE
HERRIDGE.
>> CONGRESSMAN, THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL REPORT REVEALS A
MULTIFCAMPAIGN.
THE OPERATION WAS SO BOLD THE
GROUND WORK WAS LAID IN 2014,
TWO YEARS BEFORE A SINGLE BAT
LOT WAS CAST.
ACCORDING TO THE MUELLER REPORT,
A RUSSIAN GROUP CALLED THE
INTERNET RESEARCH AGENCY USED
SOCIAL MEDIA TO DRIVE A WEDGE
BETWEEN AMERICANS AN AMPLIFY
POLITICAL DIFFERENCES.
RUSSIAN MILITARY INTELLIGENCE
WAS BEHIND HACKING OPERATIONS
TARGETING THE DNC AND CLINTON
CAMPAIGN E-MAILS.
THE FINAL ELEMENT TARGETING THE
TRUMP TEAM.
THE RUSSIAN OPERATION HAD THE
ABILITY TO REACH MILLIONS OF
AMERICANS THROUGH TWITTER,
FACEBOOK, INSTAGRAM AND OTHER
OUTLETS.
ALTHOUGH THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT
PERCEIVED IT WOULD BENEFIT FROM
A TRUMP PRESIDENCY AND WORKED TO
SECURE THAT OUTCOME, THE
INVESTIGATION DID NOT ESTABLISH
THE MEMBERS OF THE TRUMP
CONSPIRED OR
COORDINATED WITH THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT.
MORE THAN TWO YEARS AFTER THE
ELECTION, A FORMER REPUBLICAN
LAWMAKER SAID PRESIDENT OBAMA
DROPPED THE BALL AND HE'S
CONCERNED THERE'S NO DETAILED
PLAN TO PREVENT A REPEAT IN
2020.
>> THESE CANDIDATES, ALL
CANDIDATES QUALIFIED FOR
PRESIDENT, ARE GIVING CLASSIFIED
BRIEFINGS.
THEY'RE BROUGHT UP TO SPEED ON
OUR RELATIONSHIP GLOBALLY.
THEY ALSO NEED TO KNOW IF
THERE'S A POSSIBILITY THAT
THERE'S A TRAITOR OR AN ATTEMPT
TO BETRAY THEM IN THEIR MIDSTS.
>> THE FBI'S COUNTER
INTELLIGENCE INVESTIGATION THAT
LAID THE FOUNDATION FOR THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL WAS OPENED IN
LATE JULY 207 BY PETER STRZOK
WHO WAS LATER REMOVED OVER HIS
ANTI-TRUMP TEXTS.
IF THERE WAS PROBABLE CAUSE AND
SECURE A WARRANT IN 2016 FOR
CARTER PAGE, IT NEVER PANNED OUT
WITH SPECIAL COUNSEL
INVESTIGATORS FINDING NO
CONSPIRACY WITH RUSSIA.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL WILLIAM
BARR IS REVIEWING THE GENESIS OF
THE RUSSIA PROBE TO MAKE SURE
THERE WAS NO UNAUTHORIZED
SURVEILLANCE.
MR. BARR DID NOT OFFER MORE
SPECIFICS, FOX NEWS UNDERSTANDS
ITS CONSIDERED A VERY SERIOUS
MATTER.
CONGRESSMAN?
>> CATHERINE, THANK YOU.
HERE WITH US, JOHN RATCLIFFE,
MEMBER OF THE JUDICIARY■C
COMMITTEE.
HE IS FROM THE STATE OF TEXAS.
CONGRESSMAN, I WANT TO PICK UP
ON WHAT CATHERINE WAS TALKING ■.
SUPPOSEDLY THE DEPARTMENT OF
JUSTICE HAD PROBABLE ■C■C■C■C■CC
RIGHT?
TO GO AND GET THIS WARRANT TO
SPY ON SOMEBODY IN THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN.
WE GET TO COLLUSION AND THEY
FIND NOTHING.
WHAT IS DISCONNECT HERE?
>> REMEMBER WHAT BILL BARR SAID
LAST WEEK?
THAT THE TRUMP -- THE OBAMA
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT WAS SPYING ON
THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN.
THE QUESTION IS, WAS THERE A
PROPER PREDICATE?
WAS THERE PROBABLE CAUSE TO
BELIEVE THAT THERE WAS A
CONSPIRACY OR COLLUSION BETWEEN
THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND RUSSIAN?
SO THAT IS THE QUESTION THAT HAS
TO BE ANSWERED.
TO BE FAIR, JUST BECAUSE BOB
MUELLER FOUND THAT THERE WAS NO
EVIDENCE OF A CONSPIRACY OR NO
EVIDENCE OF COLLUSION, DOESN'T
MEAN THAT THERE COULDN'T BE
PROBABLE CAUSE TO LOOK FOR.
IN OTHER WORDS, A GOOD REASON TO
BELIEVE IT EXISTED.
HERE'S THE PROBLEM.
AS YOU KNOW, TREY GOWDY AND I
ARE THE ONLY TWO REPUBLICANS
THAT HAD THE OPPORTUNITY TO SEE
THAT PROBABLE CAUSE EVIDENCE, TO
SEE ALL OF THOSE FISA
APPLICATIONS IN UNREDACTED FORM.
AND THEY CENTERED AROUND
SOMETHING CALLED THE STEELE
DOSSIER, WHICH WAS ENTIRELY
FALSE AND FAKE.
NOW BOB MUELLER SAYS IT WAS
REMEMBER, THE STEELE DOSSIER
SAID THAT CARTER PAGE WAS AT THE
CENTER OF A WELL-DEVELOPED
CONSPIRACY BETWEEN THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN AND THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT.
CARTER PAGE WASN'T CHARGED, HE
WAS NEVER GOING TO BE CHARGED.
THE IDEA THAT HE WAS A RUSSIAN
AGENT IS A JOKE SO THE FOLKS
AT -- SALLY YATES AND THOSE THAT
VERIFIED THIS, THEY HAVE
EXPLAINING TO DO.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE FISA COURT
ITSELF?
IS THEISA COURT BLAME
WERE THEY JUST SNOOKERED?
>> NO.
NOT NECESSARILY, JASON.
REMEMBER WHAT THEY RECEIVED WHEN
THEY WERE ASKED TO GRANT A
WARRANT TO SPY ON CARTER PAGE.
THE FIRST THING THEY SEE IN BIG
BOLD LETTERS ARE VERIFIED
APPLICATION, ALL CAPITOLS.
SO JAMES COMEY AND SALLY YATES
SIGNED OFF ON THOSE ARE
VERIFYING TO THE COURT WHAT IS
IN THERE.
THEY'RE VERIFYING THAT
CHRISTOPHER STEELE WAS A
CREDIBLE SOURCE.
THEY'RE VERIFYING THAT THE
STEELE DOSSIER HAD BEEN
CORROBORATED.
NONE OF THAT WAS TRUE.
SO THE FOLKS THAT SIGNED OFF ON,
OURT ONLY KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE TOLD.
THEY WEREN'T TOLD THAT
CHRISTOPHER STEELE WAS OUT TO
THEY WEREN'T TOLD THAT THE
STEELE DOSSIER WAS PAID FOR BY
HILLARY CLINTON.
SO THE COURT WAS AT THE MERCY OF
THE PEOPLE THAT VERIFIED THIS
INFORMATION.
THAT'S WHAT BILL BARR WILL LOOK
AT.
THAT'S WHAT HE'S PROMISED TO
LOOK AT■C■C■C AND WHAT NEED HIM
LOOK AT.
CONGRESSMAN, THANK YOU.
YOU■C■C■CCUTED TERRORISM CASES
AND ONE OF TWO PEOPLE TO HAVE
ACTUALLY SEEN THAT DOCUMENT.
I NEVER HEARD THAT, THAT IT WAS
SAID AT THE■C■C■C TOP THAT IT W
VEN BOLD CAPITOL LETTERS
THAT IS IMPORTANT FOR PEOPLE TO
KNOW.
THANK YOU.
ALSO FROM TEXAS, THE TEXAS
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR DAN PATRICK.
SAYS SITTING HER WITH US.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> AMAZING THINGS HAPPENING IN
TEXAS.
TEXAS IS A RED STATE.
>> AND WE'RE GOING TO STATE RED
AND THE PRESIDENT IS GOING TO
KICK THEIR BUTT NO MATTER WHAT
TEAM THEY LINE UP.
COUPLE THINGS ARE HAPPENING.
THE LAST ELECTION WAS REAL.
BETO O'ROURKE RAISED $80
MILLION.
>> CRAZY.
DID 80 MILLION.
>> AND SOME THINGS HAPPENED THAT
WOULD NOT NORMALLY HAPPEN.
THIS ELECTION WILL BE DIFFERENT.
FIRST OF ALL, WHEN PRESIDENT
TRUMP RAN, PEOPLE PUT THEIR
HOPES ON HIM.
THEY DIDN'T KNOW HIM WELL.
THEY SAID WE NEED THIS GUY.
HERE'S SANITY IN A WORLD OF
INSANITY.
NOW HE'S DELIVERED.
WHEN YOU RUN FOR OFFICE, YOU SAY
WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO DO AND DO
WHAT YOU SAY YOU'RE GOING TO DO
THAT'S WHAT HE'S BEEN DONE.
WHERE HE'S STYMIED, IT'S NOT HIS
DOING AND HE WILL GET IT DONE.
HE'S A TRUSTED MEMBER OF THE
FAMILY.
PEOPLE HAVE YOUR BACK WHEN YOU
BECOME A TRUSTED MEMBER OF THE
FAMILY.
SO IN TEXAS, THE LEFTIST
DEMOCRATS, THE BILLIONAIRES AND
MILLIONAIRES ARE GOING TO POUR
MONEY TO TEXAS THINKING THEY
HAVE A SHOT.
THE PRESIDENT WILL HAVE TO POUR
MONEY.
SENATOR CORNYN IS ON THE TICKET.
>> I READ THERE'S SOMETHING
LIKE -- SINCE THE MID-TERM,
WHICH WASN'T TOO LONG AGO,
THERE'S LIKE 400,000 --
>> NEWLY REGISTERED VOTERS.
>> HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
>> WE'RE A GROWING STATE.
>> YOU'RE NOT GROWING THAT FAST.
>> ABOUT 1,000 PEOPLE A DAY.
IT'S FAST.
OUR REGISTRATION GOES UP 8 TO
10% EVERY ELECTION.
WE'RE GOING TO REGISTER A LOT OF
REPUBLICANS.
NO MATTER WHO THE DEMOCRATS
HAVE, LET'S SAY IT'S BERNIE.
WE DO A LOT OF HUNTING IN TEXAS.
THAT TICKET WON'T HUNT, THIS
COULD BE A McGOVERN TYPE OF
YEAR.
TRIP WILL DO BETTER IN MICHIGAN.
HE WON BY NINE.
IT WILL TAKE MONEY AND TIME BUT
TEXANS WILL TURN OUT.
WE TURNED OUT DESPITE THE FACT
THAT BETO MADE A CHARGE.
I RECEIVED 1.5 MILLION MORE
VOTERS.
SO REPUBLICANS WILL BE THERE.
THE MARGIN WERE DIFFERENT.
BUT THIS ELECTION -- THE WORLD
IS CRAZY.
>> I HAVE ABOUT 30 SECONDS LEFT.
TELL ME ABOUT THE POLITICS AT
THE BORDER.
HOW IS THAT PLAYING?
>> THE DEMOCRATS WANT OPEN
BORDERS.
THEY'RE WILLING TO TAKE THE
LIVES OF BABIES ON BOTCHED
ABORTIONS.
THEY WANT A WEAKENED MILITARY.
TEXANS LIKE AMERICANS ARE SMART.
THEY HAVE COMMON SENSE.
THEY KNOW ALL OF THE POLICIES
ARE FAILED POLICIES.
THE BORDER IS IMPORTANT IN
TEXAS.
WE HAVE ALREADY PASSED A TOTAL
NUMBER OF PEOPLE CROSSING THE
TEXAS ILLEGALLY THAN ALL OF LAST
YEAR.
>> AND YOU HAVE A VOTER
REGISTRATION ISSUE WE HAVE TO
DEAL WITH AS WELL.
>> TRUMP WILL WIN TEXAS.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE HIS BACK AND
HE WILL HAVE A HUGE VICTORY AND
PUT AN END TO SOCIALISM.
>> YOU HAVE TO WIN TEXAS TO WIN
THE PRESIDENCY.
>> COUNT ON IT.
>> THIS YEAR, AN ATTACK ON
CHRISTIANS.
SO WHY CAN'T BARACK OBAMA AND
HILLARY CLINTON JUST SAY AS
MUCH?
VICTOR DAVIS HANSON HAS SOME
THOUGHTS.
LATER, HE CLAIMS HE WAS KICKED
OUT OF THE CONNECTICUT HIGH
SCHOOL FOR BEING A CONSERVATIVE
AND HE HAS RECORDINGS TO BACK IT
UP.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS THE
■■■e8■■
Some people say
"dress your age."
That's ridiculous.
I dress how I feel.
Yesterday I felt bold with
boundless energy.
This morning I woke up calm
and unbreakable.
Tomorrow? Who knows.
Age is just an illusion.
How you show up for the
world, that's what's real.
What's your idea?
I put it out there with
a GoDaddy website.
Make the world you want.
>> EXPLOSIONS ACROSS THE WORLD
ARE MAKING SUNDAY TOUGH.
>> IT'S ON PEOPLE'S MIND AS THEY
GO TO CHURCH.
>> MORE THAN 200 PEOPLE WERE
KILLED AND 800 INJURED IN
SRI LANKA.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT YOU HAVE
TO THINK ABOUT IN A RELIGIOUS
HOUSE.
>> IT'S SOMETHING TO BE
CONCERNED ABOUT.
THERE'S A RISING OF THE REST
COLLECTION.
EVERYBODY SHOULD DO THAT SAFELY.
>> IT'S A HARD STORY.
HUNDREDS WERE KILLED AND
HUNDREDS MORE WERE INJURED AFTER
A WELL-COORDINATED TERROR ATTACK
RICH THROUGH CHURCHES IN
SRI LANKA.
A LITTLE TERROR GROUP TARGETED
THESE FOLKS BECAUSE OF THEIR
FAITH.
A TWEET SEND OUT BY BARACK OBAMA
AND HILLARY CLINTON, THEY BOTH
USED THE PHRASE EASTER
WORSHIPPERS.
MANY FOUND IT AS A WAY TO GLOSS
OVER THE ANTI-CHRISTIAN
MOTIVATION BEHIND THIS .
SO WHAT DOES VICTOR DAVIS HANSON
THINK?
HE'S A FELLOW OF THE HOOVER
INSTITUTION.
SIR, I APPRECIATE YOU JOI■k■k■k
A LOT OF DEMOCRATIC LEADERS.
REPRESENTATIVE KILDE, THE
GOVERNOR OF COLORADO.
THEY ALL TALK ABOUT EASTE
WORSHIPPERS.
WHY DOES THIS HAPPEN?
>> WE SAW THE SAME THING WITH
THE NOTRE DAME TRAGEDY.
IT WAS A TOURIST DESTINATION
RATHER THAN A CHURCH.
FOR THE LIBERAL MODERN
PROGRESSIVE MIND AND THE
CONSTITUENCIES THAT THEY
REPRESENT, THIS IS PART OF
WESTERN CIVILIZATION.
IT'S IRONIC, JASON.
THE MAJORITY NOW FOR THE FIRST
TIME REALLY IN THE LAST TWO
DECADES OF THE WORLD'S 2.5
BILLION CHRISTIANS ARE NOT IN
EUROPE OR THE UNITED STATES.
PEOPLE MUCH POORER THAN WE ARE
IN AFRICA OR ASIA AND LATIN
AMERICA AND SOUTH AMERICAN, THEY
BELIEVE THEY HAVE HOPE IN
CONDITIONS FAR LESS FREE THAN
OUR OWN.
WE HAVE FREEDOM AND AFFLUENCE
AND WE ABUSE THAT AND LOSE OUR
FAITH.
>> Jason: I APPRECIATE YOUR
TS ON THAT. ALSO W GET YOUR THO
ON THIS.
I WANT TO PITH YOU --■■
PLAYED T■■EO FOR
IT'S AN NBC NEWS REPORTER
CONFRONTING MR. MUELLER OUTSIDE
OF A CHURCH ON EASTER.
WATCH THIS.
>> WE WAITED FOR HIM EASTER
SERVICES, TRIED TO AS
RESPECTFUL AS POSSIBLE.
YOU TESTIFY BEFORE CONGRESS,
SIR?
>> NOqg■mñnMMENT.
>> YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
>> NO COMMENT.
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU MAKE A
RECOMMENDATION TO CONGRESS?
>> IT'S ACCURATE TO CHARACTERIZE
DIRECTOR MUELLER AS BEING TIGHT
LIPPED IN RESPONSE TO MY
QUESTIONS.
>> Jason: THEY'RE LAUGHING AT
THE END OF THAT.
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS?
>> YEAH.
AGAIN FOR THE MEDIA AND THE
PROGRESSIVE SWATH OF THE
POPULATION, AN EASTER SERVICE IS
NOT A SAFE SPACE.
THE SAFE SPACE IS A RACIALLY
SEGREGATED PLACE ON CAMPUS.
THE OTHER ASPECT, MUELLER WAS A
GOD OF DEITY UNTIL HE DIDN'T
BRING BACK A VERDICT OF
COLLUSION.
SO IN THIS NEWS CYCLE THAT THE
PROGRESSIVES FOLLOW, HE'S NO
LONGER A SAINT.
>> Jason: VERY TRUE.
I ALSO WANT YOUR -- I READ THIS
PIECE THAT YOU WROTE IN NATIONA■
YOU TALK ABOUT THE EFFORTS T■k■
■O TO THE VIEWERS, WHAT
YOUR THOUGHTS ARE ON THIS WAY O■
DEMONIZING ATTORNEY GENERAL
BARR.
>> I THINK THEY'RE VERY AFRAID
OF WILLIAM BARR.
THEY DON'T KNOW HIM THAT WELL
FROM.
WHAT THEY HAVE SEEN OF HIM, HE'S
FOLLOWED THE LAW TO THE LETTER
NO MATTER THE PUBLIC PRESSURE ON
THE PARTISANSHIP.
HE GIVE A SYNOPSIS OF THE
MUELLER REPORT ANDWERE
FURIOUS BECAUSE HE WAS RIGHT.
MORE IMPORTANTLY, THE ONLY THING
THAT WILL STOP THIS HYSTERIA
FROM CYCLES OF LOGAN ACT CLAUSE,
25th AMENDMENT, MUELLER IS GOING
TO WEAR THE REAL CULPABILITY IS.
WE'RE GOING TO GET REFERRALS
FROM THE HOUSE AND THE SENATE
AND THERE IS REAL LEGAL EXPOSURE
THERE.
A FISA COURT WAS DECEIVED.
RUSSIAN NATIONALS GAVE
INFORMATION TO A PAID EMPLOYEE
OF GPS WHO WAS IN TURN PAID BY
HILLARY CLINTON.
WE KNOW THAT JAMES COMEY LEAKED
A CLASSIFIED MEMO.
WE KNOW THAT CERTAIN PEOPLE,
ANDREW McCABE IN PARTICULAR,
PROBABLY JAMES COMEY AS WELL,
LIED TO F INVESTIGATORS OR
LIED UNDER OATH TO CONGRESS.
BAR IS NOT THE TYPE OF PERSON IN
THE CASE OF CLAPPER AND■m BR
THAT'S OKAY.
HE'S A PROFESSIONAL.
HE UNDERSTANDS THERE'S NOTHING
THAT T LEFT CAN DO THAT WILL
SWAY HIM IF THERE'S CULPABILITY.
IT'S A VERY SCARY THOUGHT.
IF THERE IS CULPABILITY.S■O■O■O
>> Jason: IT'S A GREAT PIECE.
I ENCOURAGE PEOPLE TO LOOK IT
UP.
THANKS, VICTOR.
MEXICAN TROOPS PULLING THEIR
WEAPONS ON U.S. SOLDIERS ON OUR
SIDE OF THE BORDER.
THE STUNNING REPORT BEFORE MARK
MORGAN AND TOM HOLLOMAN TELL US
Don't just dream
about your next vacation.
Book your next vacation.
♪♪
Be a Booker at Booking.com
>> Jason: A SHOCKING STORY
COMING FROM THE BORDER OF MEXICO
AS MEXICAN TROOPS DISARMING AN
AMERICAN SOLDIER WHILE ON THE
UNITED STATES SIDE OF THE
BORDER.
TRACE GALLAGHER IS IN OUR WEST
COAST NEWSROOM WITH THE LATEST.
TRACE?
>> JASON, THIS HAPPENED NINE
DAYS AGO IN EL PASO COUNTY.
TWO U.S. SOLDIERS WERE SWIFTLY
APPROACH AT GUN POINT BY FIVE OR
SIX MEMBERS OF THE MEXICAN
MILITARY WHO WERE APPARENTLY
CARRYING ASSAULT RIFLES.
THE U.S. SOLDIERS SAY■a■■ENED S
HAVE TIME TO ACTIVATE THEIR GPS
TRACKING DEVICE, WHICH ALSO
DOUBLES AS AN EMERGENCY BEACON
TO NOTIFIED 911.
THE MEXICAN■÷■÷■@■@■@Y M■EMBERS
ORDERED THE SOLDIERS OUT O■7■■
CAR, TOLD THEM TO MOVE TO THE
FRONT OF THE VEHICLE AND REMOVED
ONE OF THE SOLDIER'S SERVICE
WEAPONS PLACING IT INSIDE THE
U.S. GOVERNMENT VEHICLE.
THE SOLDIER SAYS HE GAVE UP HIS■
WEAPON TO■4■÷
SITUATIONHERE WAS CERTAIN
BECAUSE THE U.S. SOLDIERS
COULDN'T IDENTIFY ANY SEALS OR
SYMBOLS ON THE MEXICAN MILITARY
FORTUNATELY ONE OF T@p
@p@pKE A LITTLE SPANISH
AND WAS ABLE TO EXPLAIN THE
SITUATION.
ONE SOLDIER SAYS HE ALSO HEARD
SOMEONE SOUTH OF THE BORDER YELL
LET'S GO AND THEIR LEFT.
THE ENTIRE ENCOUNTER LASTED LESS
THAN 30 MINUTES.
TURNS OUT, THE U.S. SOLDIERS
WERE SOUTH OF THE BORDER FENCE,
BUT NORTH OF THE RIO GRANDE.
MEANING THEY WERE IN THE UNITED
STATES.
AUTHORITIES ACKNOWLEDGE THAT
BECAUSE THE AREA IS DRIED OUT
AND FILLED WITH BRUSH, IT'S
OFTEN DIFFICULT TO TELL WHAT
SORT OF THE BORDER YOU'RE ON.
WHEN U.S. SOLDIERS GET IN THEIR
VEHICLE, THEY CONTACTED CUSTOMS
AND BORDER PROTECTION WHO
QUICKLY RERESPONDED.
WE'RE TOLD THE U.S. SOLDIERSçI■I
FOLLOWED ALL PROCEDURES AND
PROTOCOLS.
JASON?
>> THANK YOU.
JOINING ME NOW WITH REACTION IS
MARK MORGAN, A FORMER BORDER
PATROL CHIEF UNDER OBAMA AND TOM
HOLMAN.
MARK, I WANT TO START WITH YOU.
THIS ACTUALLY HAPPENS MORE OFTEN
THAN WE WOULD KNOW, RIGHT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THIS IS A ONE-TIME EVENT.
THIS ILLUSTRATES HOW DIFFICULT
IT IS TO PATROL THE SOUTHWEST
BORDER.
I'D LIKE TO KNOW MORE ABOUT THE
SITUATION.
SOMETIMES MEXICAN OFFICIALS ARE
WORKING FOR THE CARTELS.
IF YOU LISTEN TO TRACE'S
EXPLANATION IS, I'M NOT SURE
100% THE ACTUAL MEXICAN
GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS.
>> THAT IS PART OF THE POINT
HERE, RIGHT?
IT'S NOT AS IF THE UNITED STATES
IS TRYING TO BREAK IN TO MEXICO.
WHY WOULD THEY HAVE TROOPS RIGHT
UP ON OUR BORDER.
>> RIGHT.
FROM MY EXPERIENCE, I WOULD
SUGGEST THEY WERE THERE POSSIBLY
SUPPORTING THE MEXICAN CARTELS.
THAT IS A LARGE CALL ASSUMPTION.
IT'S NOT FAR OFF PACE.
>> YOU HAD THIS EXPERIENCE, TOM.
YOU DETAINED MEXICAN OFFICIALS
ON OUR SIDE.
>> YEAH, WHEN THE STORY BROKE, I
REMEMBER 30 YEARS AGO, AS A
YOUNG AGENT, WE GOT A CALL
MEXICAN MILITARY ON A RANCH.
THE RANCHER CALLED US.
FULLY AUTOMATIC WEAPONS.
WE SHOWED UP, SEVERAL OTHER
AGENTS.
WE FOUND HIM.
WE HANDLED IT DIFFERENTLY.
WE DISARMED HIM AND ARRESTED
HIM.
WE TURNED HIM OVER TO THE
COMMANDER AND GAVE HIM THE
AUTOMATIC WEAPONS.
MARK IS RIGHT.
WHEN YOU GET A CALL LIKE THAT,
YOU DON'T KNOW IF THERE'S
MEXICANS IN FATIGUES 0, MILITARY
LOST IN A TRAINING EXERCISE OR
DON'T KNOW IF THEY'RE WORKING IN
A SECURITY DETAIL.
IT'S A SCARY SITUATION AND IT
WASN'T UNTIL AFTER THIS
SITUATION HAPPENED, IT'S LIKE
WOW THAT COULD HAVE WENT BAT.
CARRYING A SIX-SHOT RUGER.
IT HAPPENS MORE TIMES THAN YOU
CAN GUESS.
>> NOW, PART OF THE ISSUE HERE,
MARK, THAT THERE EVIDENTLY
WASN'T A WALL OR FENCE.
IF YOU CAN'T DELINEATE WHERE THE
BORDER IS, IT SOUNDS AS IF
THERE'S CONFUSION.
BECAUSE THERE WAS NO WALL,
RIGHT?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS IS ANOTHER -- IT'S NOT
MANUFACTURED, THIS IS ANOTHER
EXAMPLE THAT 60% OF THE BORDER
IS WIDE OPEN.
MEANING IT DOESN'T HAVE ENOUGH
OF THE MULTILAYER APPROACH.
IF YOU HAD THAT AT THE RIGHT
LEVELS, I THINK THIS ISSUE
WOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED.
>> THE NUMBER OF APPREHENSIONS,
FOX PLAYING THIS STORY EARLIER,
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
164,000 APPREHENSIONS IN THE
FIRST SEVEN MONTHS.
THAT'S MORE THAN ALL OF LAST
YEAR.
NOW, IT'S DONE ON A FISCAL
CALENDAR.
WE'RE STILL ABOUT SEVEN MONTHS
IN THIS CALENDAR YEAR.
WE'RE TO THE FISCAL YEAR.
THE TRAJECTORY HERE, THE NUMBERS
ARE OVERWHELMING.
>> THERE'S GOING TO BE OVER A
MILLION.
I'LL PUT IT IN THIS CONTEXT.
I'VE DONE THIS 34 YEARS.
THIS IS THE WORST I'VE EVER SEEN
IT.
HAVE WE ARRESTED --
>> Jason: WHY?
>> WE ARRESTED MORE THAN A
MILLION A COUPLE DECADES AGO.
95% WERE MEXICAN NATIONALS.
THEY WERE REMOVED AND REENTERED.
I ARRESTED THE SAME ONES THREE
OR FOUR TIMES IN A SHIFT.
THEY WERE QUICKLY REMOVED, THIS
MILLION PEOPLE COMING NOW,
THEY'RE NOT LEAVING.
THEY'RE TAKING ADVANTAGE OF THE
LOOP HOLES AND WILL BE HERE FOR
YEARS.
EVEN IF THEY DO SHOW UP IN
COURT, 90% WILL LOSE.
THEY'RE NOT LEAVING.
>> I WENT TO THE DETENTION
FACILITY IN ARIZONA.
THERE WERE PEOPLE FROM 150
DIFFERENT COUNTRIES THERE.
DON'T JUST THINK THIS IS MEXICAN
OR HONDURANS.
THERE'S PEOPLE FROM ALL OVER THE
WORLD.
THEY KNOW THIS IS HOW YOU GET IN
THE UNITED STATES.
>> TOM IS RIGHT.
THAT'S PART OF THE FALSE
NARRATIVE THAT YOU HEAR WELL,
BACK IN THE 2000s, NUMBERS WERE
HIGHER.
IT'S FALSE.
IT'S TIME TO DESCRIBE IT.
WE REMOVED 90% BACK THEN.
THIS YEAR WITH THE MILLION
ANTICIPATED BECAUSE OF THE
BROKEN LAWS, WE'LL ALLOW 650,000
TO 700,000 INTO OUR COUNTRY.
SO IT'S A COMPLETE FALSE
NARRATIVE.
THAT'S WHY OUR SYSTEM IS
OVERWHELMED.
>> Jason: WE CAN KEEP SAYING
CONGRESS, CONGRESS, CONGRESS,
BUT JUST TRYING TO ENFORCE THE
CURRENT LAW, I MEAN, IS A VERY
DIFFICULT THING.
CAN'T THANK THE MEN AND WOMEN
DOING THE JOB THAT YOU HAVE DONE
IN THE PAST.
WE THANK YOU FOR YOUR SERVICE
AND THANK YOU FOR JOINING US
TODAY.
MEXICAN TROOPS ON OUR SIDE OF
THE BORDER DISARMING OUR ARMY?
UNBELIEVABLE.
2020 CANDIDATES HAVE MADE THE
ISSUE OF REPARATIONS PART OF
THEIR PLATFORMS.
NOW A SERIOUS EFFORT IS -- BY
HOUSE DEMOCRATS COULD MAKE THIS
A LEGISLATIVE REALITY.
AND WHY IS ONE COLLEGE NEWSPAPER
ENDORSING THE IDEA OF SEGREGATED
HOUSING?
SERIOUSLY?
THAT'S COMING UP NEXT.
♪
Book now and enjoy free■CC■■
unlimited open bar and more.
Norwegian Cruise Line. Feel
Free.
>> HAS PROPOSED A COMMISSION TO
STUDY REPARATIONS.
IF THAT PASSES AND YOU ARE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES,
WOULD YOU SIGN THAT BILL?
>> YES.
WHEN I'M ELECTED PRESIDENT, I
WILL SIGN THAT BILL.
>> YES, I WOULD.
I ALREADY SUPPORT THAT BILL.
>> JHILE REPARATIONS
DIDN'T HAVE THE SUPPORT OF
BARACK OBAMA, IT'S A LITMUS TEST
FOR THE 2020 DEMOCRATIC
CANDIDATES.
NOW WITH MANY SUPPORTING IT, THE
DEBATE HAS NEW MOMENTUM IN
CONGRESS.
SHEILA JACKSON LEE PO
CREATE A COMMISSION TO STUDY THE
IMPACT OF SLAVERY AND
REPARATIONS.
JOINING ME, DON JOINS, ATTORNEY
AND FORMER GEORGIA STATE
REPRESENTATIVE.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
I WANT TO GO TO YOU FIRST.
WHY IS THIS AN IDEA?
HERE WE ARE IN 2019.
WHY IS THIS AN IDEA THAT IS
SUDDENLY CATCHING ON?
IS IT JUST ELECTION YEAR
POLITICS OR SOMETHING THAT IS
REAL?
>> YOU KNOW, THIS HAS BEEN AN
ISSUE THAT HAS COME UP IN
AMERICAN POLITICS SINCE THE 70s.
NOW WE HAVE CANDIDATES THAT ARE
REALLY WILLING TO OPEN UP AND
SPEAK ABOUT IT AND A YOUNG
PROGRESSIVE GROUP OF PEOPLE IN
COLLEGES THAT ARE LOOKING
FORWARD TO THE REPARATIONS
ISSUE.
LISTEN, ALL WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
IS STUDYING AN ISSUE WHERE
AMERICAN HAS GIVEN REPARATIONS
AFTER WORLD WAR ONE, FOR
INTERNMENT CAMPS, ALL KINDS OF
SITUATIONS.
SO WHY NOT DISCUSSING THE IDEA
FOR ONE OF THE MOST HORRIBLE
PORTIONS OF AMERICAN HISTORY,
SLAVERY.
LET'S DISCUSS IT.
>> Jason: HORACE, YOUR THOUGHTS?
>> THIS IS A SCHOOL, A RUSE.
THE DEMOCRATS AND PROGRESSIVES
HAVE NO ACTUAL AGENDA TO OFFER
BLACK AMERICANS OR FOR THAT
MATTER ANY WORKING AMERICANS IN
THIS COUNTRY.
FDR, FAMOUSLY SAID, ALL WE HAVE
TO FEAR IS FEAR ITSELF.
PROGRESSIVES TODAY, ALL THEY
HAVE TO OFFER IS FEAR.
THEY GO WITH DIVISION, THEY GO
WITH THE EFFORT TO SEPARATE US.
THERE IS NO SCENARIO WHERE
CHECKS ARE COMING OUT TO PEOPLE.
THIS IS JUST A SUBSTITUTE FOR
HAVING TO GO FORWARD WITH A REAL
ALTERNATIVE TO THE BOOMING JOB
CREATION PLAN THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP HAS PRESENTED.
>> Jason: AND PRESIDENT OBAMA
OBAMA DIDN'T SUPPORT IT.
BERNIE SANDERS DOESN'T SUPPORT
IT.
AND WHY IS IT COMING UP NOW?
DOES IT ALWAYS COME UP JUST
BEFORE AN ELECTION?
>> WELL, AS YOU MENTIONED,
BARACK OBAMA DIDN'T SUPPORT IT.
IT DID NOT COME UP BEFORE EVERY
ELECTION.
BECAUSE BARACK OBAMA WAS BLACK
DOESN'T MEAN THAT HE HAS TO
SUPPORT EVERY ISSUE THAT OTHER
BLACK PEOPLE SUPPORT.
I'M NOT SURE WHY MR. COOPER IS
AFRAID OF REPARATIONS.
>> IT'S A SCAM.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU ONLY
BELIEVE IT HAS TO BE CHECKSp@p@@
>> IT'S Ap@p@ SCAM.
THERE'S NO --
>> Jason: HOLD ON.
>> THERE'S NO LIVING FORMER
SLAVES.
>> Jason: I HAVE TO TURN TO
SOMETHING ELSE THAT GETS UNDER
MY SKIN.
IT'S HAPPENING IN WILLIAMS
COLLAGE IN MASSACHUSETTS.
THE SCHOOL'S EDITORIAL BOARD HAS
ENDORSED RACIAL SEGREGATED
HOUSING ON CAMPUS, THIS IS
HAPPENING.
THE WILLIAMS RECORD WRITES THAT
THE COLLEGE A PREDOMINANTLY
WHITE INSTITUTION AND STUDENTS
OF COLOR FEEL TOKENIZED.
IT WILL HAVE A MORE SAFE
COMMUNITY FOR MINORITIZED
STUDENTS.
AND THIS IS HAPPENING HERE IN
D.C., TOO.
GEORGE WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY.
IF THEY HAD DONE THIS IN IDAHO
OR UTAH, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
NOW IT'S HAPPENING IN
MASSACHUSETTS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR THOUGHTS
ARE ON THIS.
IS THIS IS A GOOD IDEA?
SEGREGATED HOUSING?
>> LET'S BE CLEAR.
THE AFFINITY HOUSING THAT
THEY'RE REQUESTING IS NOT ONLY
RACE BASED, IT'S BASED ON
GENDER.
WHY IS IT THAT THESE YOUNG
ADULTS CAN NOT HAVE A DISCUSSION
ABOUT WHAT MAKES THEM
COMFORTABLE IN THEIR SCHOOL?
I'M A PROUD GRADUATE OF A
HISTORICALLY BLACK COLLEGE AND
UNIVERSITY.
ONE OF THOSE SCHOOLS THAT ONLY
AFRICAN AMERICANS GO TO.
I SEE NOTHING WRONG JUST LIKE
REPARATIONS WITH EXPLORING THE
IDEAS OF WHAT WORKS FOR THEM.
LISTEN, AMERICA --
>> MOVING THEp@p@p@p@p@p@p@p@ S
SCHOOLS -- I HAVE 20 SECONDS
LEFT.
>> I LOVE THIS.
WE WANT TO WRAP DISCRIMINATION
BIGOTRY IN THE RUBRIC OF THE
FIRST AMENDMENT.
BROWN V. BOARD RULED SEGREGATION
IS INHERENTLY UNEQUAL.
IT'S 2019.
WE NEED TO MOVE ON PASSED ALL OF
THESE THINGS, PUT UP A REAL
AGENDA.
IF YOU WANT TO COMPETE WITH WHAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP DOING, PUT UP
A REAL AGENDA.
>> Jason: SEGREGATING SCHOOLS
AND PUTTING -- I HOPE WE
CONTINUE THIS DISCUSSION BECAUSE
I THINK IT'S WORTH HAVING.
I DIDN'T THINK WE WOULD HAVE TO
HAVE IT IN THE YEAR 2019.
THANKS FOR YOUR INPUT.
WE HAVE TO MOVE ON.
A HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT SAYS HE
WAS EXPELLED FOR BEING A
CONSERVATIVE.
HE HAS AUDIO CLIPS TO BACK IT
UP.
THAT'S COMING UP NEXT.
■■■■■----Q
Oh, sir. That was my grandma's.
Don't worry, ma'am. All of your
stuff is in OK hands.
Just OK?
They don't give two and a half
stars to just anybody.
Here you go.
What's this?
It's your piano.
Hold this for a sec!
We don't have a piano.
No.
But the neighbors do.
Just OK is not OK.
Especially when it comes to you
network.
AT&T is America's best wireless
network
according to America's biggest
test.
Now with 5G Evolution.
The First Step to 5G.
More for your thing.
That's our thing.
>> 16-YEAR-OLD MICHAEL MANCINI
SAID HE WAS EXPELLED FROM HIGH
SCHOOL FOR EXPRESSING HIS
CONSERVATIVE VIEWS.
IT STARTED BECAUSE HE DISAGREED
WITH WHAT IS SHAKESPEARE
PORTRAYING GENDERISM IN A
POSITIVE LIGHT.
THIS IS THE SECRETLY RECORDED
AUDIO HE TOOK WHEN SPEAKING WITH
THE HEAD OF THE DISCIPLINARY
COMMITTEE.
>> WHEN YOU SPEAK YOUR MIND AND
YOU ARE OFFENDING PEOPLE IN THE
ROOM, THAT CAN BE SEEN AS PART
OF HARASSMENT.
>> I HAD THESE TWO GIRLS
SCREAMING IN MY FACE.
THAT MADE ME FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE.
HARASSING ME.
>> YOU MAKE COMMENTS IN CLASS
AND MAKE THOSE PEOPLE FEEL
UNCOMFORTABLE.
THE INITIAL BURDEN IS ON YOU.
>> Jason: WE REACHED OUT TO THE
SCHOOL AND HAVE NOT HEARD BACK.
JOINING ME NOW IS MICHAEL
MANCINI AND HE'S FATHER, TED.
THANKS FOR JOINING US HERE.
YOU SAID, MICHAEL -- I'M SORRY
YOU'RE HAVING TO GO THROUGH
THIS.
BUT WHAT IS IT THAT WAS SO
DISAGREEABLE AT THAT SCHOOL?
>> WELL, I SAID THAT IT WAS
HISTORICALLY INACCURATE FOR
SHAKESPEARE TO PROMOTE
TRANSGENDERISM IN A POSITIVE
LIGHT.
WE TALKED ABOUT THE BOCK WRITTEN
IN 1601 TO 1602.
THEY WOULD HAVE NOT NORMALIZED
THAT OR PORTRAYED THAT IN A
POSITIVE LIGHT.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN LOOKED AT
MENTAL INSANITY.
>> Jason: TED, YOU HEARD THERE
WAS A PROBLEM AND THEN YOUR SON
IS BEING EXPELLED.
AS YOU DOVE IN, WHAT DID YOU
FIND?
>> I FOUND THAT IT'S REALLY
HEAVY LIBERAL BIAS.
WITH THE TAPES THAT YOU JUST
PLAYED, IF YOU DO ON THE
WEBSITE,
THEREALCHESHSHIREACADEMY.
COMP , YOU CAN SEE IT ALL.
IF SOMEONE IS OFFENDED, YOU'RE
ON THE HOOK FOR THAT AND IT'S
YOU'RE FAULT IF THEY ATTACK YOU.
>> Jason: MICHAEL, WAS THERE A
FIGHT?
PUSHING, SHOVING?
>> NO PUSHING OR SHOVING.
JUST YELLING.
>> Jason: AND YOU SAID THERE
WERE TWO GIRLS THAT YELLED AT
YOU AND TRYING TO INTIMIDATE
YOU.
DID ANYTHING HAPPEN TO THEM?
>> I WAS NOT TOLD.
I WAS TOLD THEY WERE PUNISHED.
I WAS NEVER TOLD EXACTLY WHAT.
>> THEY WEREN'T GIVEN A
DISCIPLINARY HEARING LIKE
MICHAEL WAS.
>> NOT EVEN CLOSE.
>> SO WHAT ARE THE LESSONS
YOU'RE LEARNING HERE?
YOU WERE ASKED TO TAKE A
POSITION IN THIS CLASS, CORRECT?
>> YES, I WAS ASKED TO TAKE MY
POSITION.
>> THEY ASKED HIM HIS OPINION.
AFTER HE STATED HIS OPINION, THE
TEACHER SAID CAN YOU PLEASE
ELABORATE?
AFTER HE ELABORATED, THE GIRL
GOT UPSET AND SCREAMING AND
YELLING AT HIM.
THE TEACHER WAS TEN FEET INN'T
FRO OF HIM AND COULDN'T HEAR
HIM.
NOW THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE BRINGING
HIM UP FOR.
HE WAS ATTACKED BY THEM.
BUT THAT WAS OKAY.
>> Jason: MICHAEL, I HAVE A
SHORT AMOUNT O TIME HERE.
YOU WERE ALSO ASKED TO TAKE A
QUIZ DURING A WHITE PRIVILEGE
SEMINAR.
WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
>> I WAS NOT PART OF A WHITE
PRIVILEGE SEMINAR.
THAT WAS A REQUIRED WORK
STATION.
I DIDN'T GO TO THAT.
THAT WAS ONE OF THE WORK
STATIONS ON MARTIN LUTHER KING
DAY.
>> HE WAS IN WORKSHOP.
THERE THEY HAD THE BUZZ FEED
SURVEY AS TO HOW PRIVILEGED YOU
ARE.
SOME OF THEM WERE WHITE
PRIVILEGED, TOXIC MASCULINITY.
WHEN MICHAEL WAS OFFENDED, HE
ASKED WHY IS THAT OKAY.
AND THEN THEY STARTED THAT SINCE
YOU'RE A MAJORITY A WHITE
STRAIGHT MALE, THE BAR TO OFFEND
YOU IS SET HIGHER THAN FOR
OTHERS.
STATING THAT HE DOESN'T HAVE THE
SAME RIGHTS AND PRIVILEGES AS
EVERYBODY ELSE.
>> Jason: MICHAEL, I WISH YOU
THE BEST.
FOR EVERY DARK SPOT, SOMETHING
GOOD TO LEARN FROM IT.
I HOPE YOU LEARNED FROM IT AND
TAKE IT AS A POSITIVE AND
REMEMBER IF YOU DON'T LIKE BEING
TREATED THAT WAY, MAKE SURE
NOBODY ELSE IS TREATED THAT WAY.
BUT IT'S GOOD OF YOU AND YOUR
FATHER TO JOIN US HERE TONIGHT.
WE APPRECIATE IT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH THE
It's going to be Passover
in just a few days.
And these people are in
desperate need.
These are very difficult times
for Israel and the Jewish
people.
As the government spends
more and more of it's resources
for battling terrorism.
The situation has become a
crisis.
Every week the lines get longer
and longer.
There are more people who come
than they expect
because the numbers keep
growing.
Its difficult to have to see
people in this situation
■■■z■■
Especialis holiday
sePassover.
This should be a blessing to
you.
This $25 food box
will provide one desperately
needy family
here in Israel
with food, with hope
and with a note inside each of
these
saying that's its from
Christians and Jews in America
o seek to bless them.
With your phone call right now
a food box will go out to one
desperate family in Israel.
■■■■he food box
is a special note that will
bless them
and let them know
that America stands strong in
solidarity with Israel
in their struggle for survival.
Many of these people are ill
they're sick, they're alone.
They don't have the money to
afford
things that many of us, most of
us, take for granted.
People, who don't have enough
money to even buy some matza
the unleavened bread as the
Bible describes it.
Israel and it's people n
help now.
You can make a life changing
difference
by calling and saying that you
give a $25 food box
to help a family in need in
Israel.
Thank you and God bless you for
your support.
My experience with USAA
has been excellent.
They really appreciate
the military family
and it really shows.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
It was funny because
when we would call
another insurance company,
■÷?■can't beat USAA”
It was funny because
when we would call
We're the Webber family.
We're the Tenney's
We're the Hayles,
and we're USAA members for life.
♪
Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
>> TIME FOR THE LAST BITE.
DURING TODAY'S WHITE HOUSE
EASTER APRIL DONALD TRUMP HAD A
SURPRISING CONVERSATION WHILE
HELPING KIDS COLOR CARDS.
>> WHAT IS HAPPENING?