fusion Drops
with kiwi to lock moisture.
And soy to even skin tone.
Unleash dewy, glowing skin from
within.
New Aveeno® MaxGlow™.
>> LIKE IT OR NOT THE ESQUIRE
COVER THAT SOME PEOPLE ARE
CALLING INSENSITIVE AND
IGNORANT.
WE WILL GET INTO THAT.
PLUS:
>> GEORGE CLOONEY DEFENDS A
MEMBER OF THE ROYAL FAMILY,
AND MAKES SOME EYE-OPENING
PRINCESS DI COMPARISONS.
AND SHOULD YOU GET A SUPERBOWL
RING?
IF YOU WEREN'T IN THE SUPER
BOWL?
THAT AND MORE TONIGHT ON FOX5
LIKE IT OR NOT.
>> ♪ ♪.
>> HEY, GUESS WHAT?
WE MIGHT NOT BE TALKING ABOUT
A WALL SOON.
>> REALLY?
>> THERE IS A COMPROMISE THAT
APPARENTLY IS HAPPENING,
RIGHT?
>> SOME BREAKING NEWS?
>> LAST NIGHT?
GEEZ.
>> LET'S FACE IT.
>> OH, MY BAD.
>> OH, IT HAPPENED 38 MINUTE
AGO.
MY BAD.
IT GIVES US MORE TIME TO TALK
ABOUT WHITE GUYS.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW.
IT IS SO TOUGH BEING A WHITE
GUY THESE DAYS.
JUST ASK ESQUIRE MAGAZINE.
WE'LL FIRE IT UP WITH THAT.
OH, THE TRIALS AND
TRIBULATIONS CENTS OF THE
WHITE MALE.
CHRONICLED BY THE COVER STORY
LATEST ISSUE OF ESQUIRE.
THAT IS POOR 17 YEAR OLD RYAN
MORGAN FROM WISCONSIN, THE
QUINESSENTIAL QUOTE AMERICAN
BOY.
WHAT IT IS LIKE TO GROW UP
WHITE, MIDDLE CLASS, AND MALE
IN THE ERA OF SOCIAL MEDIA
SCHOOL SHOOTINGS, TOXIC MASSES
CUE LYNN AT THIS, ME TOO AND
DIVIDED COUNTRY.
>> THIS PIECE IS ABOUT THE
ADVERSE AT THIS OF BEING A
TRUMP SUPPORTER.
ESQUIRE EDITOR IN CHIEF SAID
MORGAN'S COVER STORY IS
ACTUALLY AN INSTALLMENT IN A
SERIES ON GROWING UP IN THE
PRESENT POLITICAL AT MOSS
CENTS FEAR.
IT WILL FEATURE BLACK LGBTQ
AND FEMALE STORIES AS WELL,
BUT THEY STARTED WITH THE
WHITE GUY.
TWITTER HAD IT WAY WITH THE
MAG A SEEN.
ONE QUOTE ESQUIRE CEO.
QUOTE WE SHOULD PROBABLY DO A
COVER STORY FOR BLACK HISTORY
MONTH.
ANY SUGGESTIONS CENTS?
EDITOR, THERE IS A WHITE BOY
IN WISCONSIN WHO IS SAD.
ESQUIRE CEO, QUOTE, RUN IT.
IS THIS REALLY MAN AT HIS
BEST, NICK?
LIKE IT OR NOT.
>> I AM GOING TO GIVE THEM A
PASON THIS AND I SAY THIS
SIMPLY BECAUSE I DO THINK IT
IS TOUGH AC TEENAGER IN 2019.
THE ISSUE IS ACTUALLY THE
MARCH ISSUE.
AND I THINK THAT MORE
IMPORTANTLY, WE HAVE GOT TO
LEARN TO START LISTENING TO
EACH OTHER, START HAVING
CONVERSATIONS SO WE'RE NOT
SHOCK BY SITUATIONS CENTS LIKE
NORTHAM, NOT SHOCK BY
TEENAGERS WHO TALK OTHERS INTO
SUICIDE, THE ONE WHO JUST GOT
CONVICTED A LOT HAPPENING WITH
YOUNG PEOPLE TODAY.
SOCIAL MEDIA DOES NOT HELP.
WE HAVE THE ABILITY TO
NAVIGATE IT.
I THINK BETTER THAN MOST,
BECAUSE WE'RE NOT IN THE EYE
OF THAT STORM.
WE CAN LEAVE IT.
WE CAN CHOOSES TO ENGAGE.
SO I'M GOING TO GIVE THEM A
PASS.
THEY SAY THIS IS AN
INSTALLMENT.
MARINA I'M HOPING THAT THEY'LL
HIGHLIGHT YOUNG WOMEN ALSO
STRUGGLING AND PEOPLE OF
COLOR.
>> WE'RE NOT WOMEN -- WE'RE
NOT THE TARGET AUDIENCE FOREST
CHOIR, I THINK MEN ARE, AND I
DON'T SEE WHAT THE PROBLEM S I
DON'T SEE WHY WE'VE GOT TO
SILENCE ANYBODY.
I MEAN IF THIS KID HAS CENTS A
STORY TELL THE STORY CLEARLY
THEY THOUGHT THAT THIS WOULD
CAUSE AN UPROAR, AS IT DID,
AND THEY DID IT ON BLACK
HISTORY MONTH.
WHICH I THINK THEY DID ON
PURPOSE.
BECAUSE THEY WANTED PEOPLE TO
SAY WHY AREN'T WE PROMOTING
AND WHY AREN'T WE HIGHLIGHTING
OTHER STORIES, BUT WE'RE
TELLING THIS CHILD'S STORYRY
WHICH I THINK HE HAS A STORY
TO TELL.
I DON'T SEE WHY.
>> WHICH IS WHAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW, STORY TO TELL
LIKE EVERYBODY DOES, WHAT,
YOU'RE WHITE AND YOU'RE A MAN
AND WE CAN'T TALK ABOUT YOU?
>> OUT OF PLACE, JUST TONE
DEAF.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S THE POINT OF TELLING
THIS STOREY?
OH, I'M SORRY YOU'RE A HIGH
SCHOOLER WITH TROUBLE BECAUSE
YOU WEAR A MAGA HAT TO HIGH
SCHOOL?
I NEED TO HEAR THAT SOB
STOREY?
>> HE REALLY DOES HAVE A STORY
TO TELL.
>> RIGHT.
>> WELL, IT IS NOT NECESSARILY
A SOB STORY, BUT IT IS HIS
STORY AND IT IS UNIQUE, THAT
WHAT MAKES AMERICA.
WE ARE ALL UNIQUE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> WE'RE A MELTING POT.
NOW TIMING IS THE ISSUE.
JUST CAME OUT AT THE WRONG
TIME.
YOU KNOW, WHO EVER ADVERTISED
IT GO AHEAD AND MAKE THIS,
PRODUCE THIS FOR THE MONTH OF
FEBRUARY EVEN THOUGH IT COMES
OUT IN MARCH IT, HIT THE
STANDS.
>> CENTS IT IS OUT NOW.
>> YES.
>> WHICH IS BLACK HISTORY
MONTH.
WOULD YOU THINK WHEN WE'RE
RECOGNIZING DEMOGRAPHIC THEY
WOULD STICK TO THAT
DEMOGRAPHIC.
>> DISCUSSION AT WOODROW
WILSON HIGH SCHOOL WHETHER TO
CHANGE THE NAME OF THE SCHOOL.
NOW HAS INVITED STUDENT,
PARENT, TEACH TEARS JOIN THE
CONVERSATION.
THE GROUP SAYS PRESIDENT
WOODROW WILL SO SEGREGATION
VIEWS AND VOCAL DEFENSE OF THE
KKK RAISES QUESTIONS ABOUT
WHETHER HE SHOULD HAVE HAD A
HIGH SCHOOL NAMED AFTER HIM.
NOW THE SCHOOL FIRST OPENED
ITS DOORS BACK IN 1935.
NAME CHANGE GUY LIKE IT OR
NOT.
>> I LIKE THIS A LOT.
BEAUTY ABOUT ALL OF THIS THAT
WE'RE HAVING DISCUSSION ABOUT
CHANGE.
AND WE ALL KNOW CHANGE AIN'T
EASY TO ACTUALLY IMPLEMENT.
WITH THIS, YOU LOOK AT IT, YOU
GOT TO SAY WELL HEY THEY'VE
IDENTIFY ADD PROBLEM, NOW
ADDRESSING THE PROBLEM AND I
EXPECT MORE SCHOOLS PROBABLY
TO FOLLOW SUIT.
I WOULD ALSO SAY THAT I DON'T
THINK WE SHOULD COMPLETELY
ERASE THE HISTORY OF WOODROW
WILSON, PART OF THE HISTORY,
IF ANYTHING, THEY SHOULD
RENAME THE SCHOOL AND MAKE
SURE THAT KIDS THAT NOW
ATTENDS THAT SCHOOL KNOW THE
HISTORY, KNOW IT ONCE WAS
CENTS NAMED WOODROW WILSON,
LOU WHAT WE ARE AND BECOME.
>> INTERESTING, BECAUSE
SOMEBODY IN THE STORY WAS
SAYING THEY HAD NO IDEA OTHER
THAN WOODROW WILSON WAS
PRESIDENT, WHAT HE STOOD FOR,
WHAT HAPPENED, AND HE CLEARLY
HAD A LOT OF FOREIGN POLICY,
BUT OBVIOUSLY DIDN'T KNOW HIS
HISTORY RIGHT?
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,  THIS IS
COMMUNITY POLITICS.
SO THIS COMMUNITY WANT TO
CHANGE IT.
AND THEY GO ABOUT THE PROPER
PROCESS.
AND IT IS APPROVED.
WHY NOT?
>> IF THIS COMMUNITY WANTS TO&
CHANGE IT AND THEY GO ABOUT
THE PROCESS THEN I SEE NO
PROBLEM WITH T BUT IF WE ARE
TALKING ABOUT JUST SWEEPING
CHANGES, TO ERASE THAT
HISTORY, I'M NOT SURE THAT
THAT'S THE SMART THING TO DO
PARTICULARLY SINCE WILSON WAS
A PRESIDENT.
IF WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
MONUMENT, I'M TOTALLY FOR IT,
MONUMENTS I THINK TAKE ON
DIFFERENT SIGNIFICANCE, BUT I
DON'T THINK WE SHOULD ERASE
THE HISTORY OF WILSON IF IT IS
ABOUT CHANGING IT BECAUSE HE
HAD VIEWS THAT ARE COUNTER TO
MY OWN.
WE ARE NOW IN A SYSTEM AND
SITUATION WHERE WE HEARD
PEOPLE STIRRING UP CONTROVERSY
AROUND PRESIDENT CLINTON.
I DON'T DOUBT THAT IN 20 YEARS
THE IDEA OF SEXUAL ASSAULT
WON'T BE SOMETHING THAT'S
PASSE, THAT WE WILL TAKE A
HARDER STANCE.
I DON'T WANT US RELEASING THE
LEGACY.
>> YOU CAN DO THIS WITH MOST
PRESIDENTS, PROBABLY FINDS
SOMETHING WRONG WITH THEIR
POLICIES.
WAS NAMED IN 1935, VERY
DIFFERENT TIME.
BUT I'M WITH THE COMMUNITY
HERE.
THIS IS THEIR DECISION,  THIS
IS THEIR SCHOOL.
THEY CAN MAKE A CHOICE WHETHER
THEY'RE OFFENDED BY THAT NAME
TO BE ON THE SCHOOL AND CHANGE
THE NAME.
JUST BECAUSE IT WAS UP THERE
ONCE DOESN'T MEAN IT IS CENTS
THERE --
>> INDEED.
COMING UP HERE SOME SAY THE
TAXI INDUSTRY IN THE DISTRICT
IS DOOMED.
THE PATRIOTS WHO DIDN'T PLAY
IN THE SUPER BOWL, BUT STILL
GETTING A RING.
PLUS GEORGE CLOONEY MAKES
SURPRISING COMPARISON, BETWEEN
MEGHAN MARKLE AND PRINCESS DI.
FOX5 LIKE IT OR NOT WILL BE
RIGHT BACK.
>> QUESTION:  IS THE TAXI CAB
INDUSTRY IN THE DISTRICT
DOOMED?
ACCORDING TO WTLP TRIPLE A
SAYS THERE HAS BEEN 32% DROP
IN THE NUMBER OF TIMES A TAXI
WAS HAILED IN D.C. IN THE
LASTS THREE YEARS.
EVEN THOUGH FARES CHARGED BY
CAB DRIVERS ARE GENERALLY
CHEAPER ON QUICK TRIPS THAN
APP BASED FARES, ALSO REPORT
BY THE DC COUNCIL, SAYS RIDE
HAILING SERVICES CENTS LIKE
UBER AND LYFT LEAD TO TRAFFIC
CONGESTION AND ADD WEAR AND
TEAR TO THE DISTRICT'S ROADS.
BUT IS THERE A WAY TO STOP
THIS FROM HAPPENING?
THE DOOMED TAXI CAB INDUSTRY.
MARINA, LIKE IT OR NOT?
>> IT IS 2019.
I DO NOT UNDERSTAND.
I GET WHY THEY'RE UPSET.
BUT BY THIS POINT THEY SHOULD
HAVE FIGURED THIS OUT F LYFT
AND UBER THRIVING, AND THEY'VE
DONE IT ONLY BASED ON AN APP,
WHAT'S DIFFERENT BETWEEN AN
UBER CAR AND TAXI CAB?
NOTHING RIGHT?
SO YOU IMPLEMENT THAT SAME
SORT OF COMPETITIVENESS,
RIGHT, YOU PUT THE APP IN
PLACE YOU HAVE COMPETITIVE
PRICES CENTS AND BOOM, YOU'RE
BACK IN THE BUSINESS.
WHY CAN'T THEY DO THIS?
WHY DO THEY WANT TO STICK TO
THE OLD WAYS?
THINGS WILL EVOLVE.
THINGS WILL CHANGE, IT IS
2019, SOMETHING WILL COME UP
IN TO 20, THEY'LL BE OUT OF
THE LOOP AGAIN, DO YOU HAVE
STAY UP WITH IT.
>> YOU HIT HOMERUN ON THIS
ONE.
THIS IS JUST DOWN RIGHT CRAZY.
LIKE YOU SAY, IT IS 2019.
TALKING ABOUT CAB DRIVERS
COMPLAINING ABOUT NOT GETTING
THE SAME AMOUNT OF MONDAY THAT
I UBER DRIVERS ARE NOW
GETTING?
WAKE UP AND SMELL THE DEAD
ROSES CENTS BECAUSE THIS IS A
DEAD INDUSTRY.
IT IS LIKE YOU GET IN A CAB,
THEY POP IN A CASTLE, ALL
LISTENING TO MP 3'S, THEY NEED
TO I AM PRESENT MEANT
SOMETHING NEW.
BRING IN NEW WAY POSSIBLY NEW
APP SO THEY COMPETE WITH
ACTUAL UBER.
THE ACTUAL CAB DRIVERS.
MAKES $27,000 A YEAR.
I WOULD ADD AN UBER DRIVER
MAKES MORE THAN THAT.
>> THEY'RE TOO LATE.
THEY'VE BEEN SURPASSED.
THERE HAD TO BE MORE THAN ONE
SOFTWARE ENGINEER THAT FIGURED
OUT HOW TO DO THIS.
WHY THESE INDUSTRY
SPECIFICALLY IN NEW YORK AND
IN A PLACE LIKE THERE WHERE
THERE ARE A LOT OF TAXI CAB
DRIVERS, WHY THEY DIDN'T ADAPT
TO THE TECHNOLOGY MAKES
ABSOLUTELY NO SENSE.
WITH THE WEATHER, JUST LIKE
THE LASTS COUPLE EVERY DAYS,
YOU THINK I'M STANDING OUTSIDE
TO HAIL A CAB WHEN I CAN PUSH
A BUTTON ON MY PHONE, THEN
WHEN THE PERSON SHOWS UP I
WALK OUTSIDE?
HELLO.
WAKE UP TO THE FUTURE PEOPLE.
OKAY?
I'M NOT GOING TO USE YOUR
SERVICE, I DON'T CARE IF IT
COST ME DOLLAR MORE, DON'T
GIVE ME THE CONGESTION STUFF
EITHER.
THE MARKET WILL DICTATE HOW
MANY PEOPLE WANT TO USE CARS.
WHETHER THEY'RE TAXICABS OR
UBER OR LIVES.
IT IS ALL THE SAME TO ME.
>> COMPLETELY AGREE, YOU ALL
HAVE SAID IT ALL.
THEY MISSED THE OPPORTUNITY,
AND I FOR ONE WILL GO OUT OF
MY WAY NOT TO TAKE A TAXI.
SO --
>> I HATE EVERYTHING ABOUT THE
TAXI, HATE, TAKE EXTRA TURN,
SHOULD I GO UP SUCH AND SUCH?
I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT THE
ROUTE, TOO, I'M DRUNK.
>> THEY HAVE RUNNING METERS,
RIGHT?
THEY USED TO HAVE THE ZONE
SITUATION HERE, THAT NEVER
MADE ANY SENSE, NEVER,
COMPLETELY, MADE NO SENSE,
CROSS OVER SOME LINE, NOW --
>> YOU HAVE TO PAY EXTRA.
>> COMING UP JOSH GORDON ONE
OF THE PLAYERS INVOLVED IN THE
PERFORMANCE ENHANCING DRUG
SCANDAL.
BUT APPARENTLY HE STILL IS
GETTING A RING BABY WHY?
BECAUSE'S' A PATRIOTS.
SHOULD HE?
Switch to Fios and get
entertainment delivered
to your home like no one else.
Because Fios is a 100%
fiber-optic network.
That means you'll get the
fastest internet available
and Fios TV One with amazing
4K capability,
and an advanced voice remote.
And now we'll give you a Netflix
premium plan for a full year.
So you can stream your favorite
Netflix shows
and movies in 4K on 4
devices at once.
Already have Netflix?
We'll cover the cost for one
year.
Just switch for 79.99 a month
with a two-year agreement
and get Fios Gigabit Connection
with TV and phone
with a 2-year price guarantee.
And not only will you get a
Netflix premium plan on us for a
year,
you'll be able to find Netflix
in the Fios Channel guide
and use the advanced voice
remote to launch Netflix
and easily find all the
channels,movies and shows
you love.
When you think about it,
there are so many entertaining
reasons to switch to Fios.
100% fiber-optic network.
100% phenomenal.
Go to getfios.com today.
>> WHAT TO DO ABOUT MASS
UNEMPLOYMENT, THIS WILL BE A
MASS SOCIAL CHALLENGE.
AND I THINK ULTIMATELY, WE
WILL HAVE TO HAVE SOME KIND OF
UNIVERSAL BASIC INCOME.
I DON'T THINK WE CAN HAVE A
CAN CHOICE.
>> WELCOME BACK, THAT WAS '
LONG MUSK BACK IN 2017 TALKING
ABOUT UNIVERSAL BASIC INCOME.
IT IS CENTS AN EXPERIMENT, ON
THE MATTER, AND IT WAS JUST
DONE IN FINLAND.
IT WAS CENTS CARRIED OUT BY
THE GOVERNMENT, AND GAVE
UNEMPLOYED PEOPLE, NO STRINGS
ATTACHED GUARANTEE INCOME,
INSTEAD EVERY UNEMPLOYMENT THE
RESULTS, WELL, PEOPLE SAY THEY
WERE HAPPIER AND LESS
STRESSED, BUT IT DID NOT MAKE
THEM ANY MORE LIKELY TO GET A
NEW GIG, MEANWHILE DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE ANKLE
DREW YANK BEHIND UNIVERSAL
BASIC INCOME BUT IS IT
SOMETHING THAT WORKS?
UNIVERSAL BASIC INCOME, GRAM,
LIKE IT OR NOT?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHETHER IT
WORKS OR NOT.
I WILL SAY THIS.
I FIRMLY AGREE WITH ANDREW
YANK, AND ' LONG MUSK, AND
OTHER, THROUGH THE YEARS, AND
IN OTHER COUNTRIES THAT
BELIEVE THAT THIS IS
NECESSARY, FOR THIS MAIN ONE
REASON.
THERE ARE A LOT OF JOBS THAT
ARE GOING TO GO AWAY HERE,
BECAUSE OF AUTOMATION.
IT IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
THERE ARE GOING TO BE DRIVER
LESS CARS, THERE WILL BE
INDUSTRIES, AI IS TAKING OVER
THE COMPANIES WILL FINDS WAYS
TO DO THESE JOBS WITHOUT
PEOPLE.
AND THIS IS WHERE WE
ECONOMICALLY ARE GOING TO HAVE
A MASSIVE PROBLEM.
IS THIS THE ANSWER?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE THE STEP
TOWARD A SOLUTION.
OTHERWISE, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
A LOT OF PEOPLE ON WELFARE,
AND THIS SEEMS LIKE A MORE
FAIR BALD WAY TO ADDRESS THOSE
NEEDS.
>> WHO IS GOING TO PAY FOR
THAT?
>> YOU TAKE AWAY THE WELFARE
PROGRAMS, PUT TAX ON THE
CONDITIONS, BY ADDING 10%
ACTION TAGS ON WHAT THEY
PRODUCE AND THE MONEY COMES
BACK TO THE PEOPLE.
>> MONEY DOESN'T ADD UP.
YOU WON'T GET TRILLIONS AND
TRILLIONS OF DOLLARS TO PAY
FOR THIS INCOME.
>> YOU ARE IF YOU MAKE THE
COMPANIES WHO DON'T HIRE
PEOPLE PAY THEIR FAIR SHARE,.
>> SOFTWARE AND OTHER
INDUSTRIES, ADAPT TO THE TIMES
AGAIN, IF IT MEANS LEARNING
BINARY CODE AND STARTING TO
LEARN HOW TO CODE THEN THAT'S
WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT'S JUST
WHERE WE LIVE.
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF
MANUFACTURING JOBS.
>> THIS NEW GREEN DEAL EVEN IF
YOU'RE UNWILLING TO WORK, WE,
THE TAXPAYER, ARE GOING TO
FUND TO YOU SIT ON THE COUCH
TO NOT DO NOTHING.
>> THAT WAS A FAUX PAS.
>> IT IS NOT.
>> A REALITY.
>> NO, AND PEOPLE SAID IT,
THEY'RE HAPPIER BUT NOT
WILLING TO LOOK FOR JOBS.
SO CLEARLY THIS ISN'T WORKING
IT YOU'RE NOT INSPIRING PEOPLE
TO GET OUT THERE AND FIND --
>> PEOPLE CAN'T LIVE ON
$12,000 A YEAR, THAT'S THE
REALITY OF IT.
>> IF THERE ARE PEOPLE OUT
THERE ON THE STREET LIVING ON
NO DOLLARS, I'M SURE THAT
PEOPLE CAN LIVE ON 1200 BUCKS.
>> WHAT'S THE SOLUTION WHEN
MILLIONS OF JOBS DISAPPEAR DUE -
>> YOU HAVE HALF OF EUROPE
LIVING UNDER A THOUSAND EUROS
A MONTH ON FAMILIES OF SIX, P
PEOPLE.
>> NOT REALITY THE COST OF
LIVING.
>> HEALTHCARE, THOUGH, MARINE,
A YOU KNOW, THE DEAL IS WE
HAVE TO FIGURE OUT SOMETHING.
THE ANSWER CAN'T BE, IT IS TOO
TOUGH TO DO SO WE DO NOTHING.
WE'VE GOT --
>> NO, THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO
OBVIOUSLY NEED ASSISTANCE, AND
THEY SHOULD BE ASSISTED AND
THAT'S CALDWELL FAIR AND WE'RE
THE TAXPAYERS AND WE SUPPORT
THAT SYSTEM, NOW SITE HERE AND
SAY I'M UNWILLING TO WORK NOW
I HAVE TO PAY SIX OOH DOLLARS
FOR EVERY SINGLE PERSON WHO
SAYS THEY'RE UNWILLING TO
WORK.
>> YOU'RE GETTING THE MONDAY
TIE.
>> PEOPLE ARE ABLE AND
UNWILLING.
>> I WILL WORK, I DON'T NEED
ANYBODY TO PAY FOR ME, I'LL
WORK, THAT'S HOW THE SYSTEM
TOO, CLEARLY DO YOU TOO OR YOU
WON'T BE HERE.
>> I WAS UNEMPLOYED.
I CAN TELL YOU IT IS A
MOTIVATIONAL TOOL.
IT FORCES CENTS TO YOU GET A
NEW JOB.
AT SOME POINT YOU WILL LOSE
THE MONEY IF YOU STAY HOME AND
SIT ON YOUR REAREND, YOU COULD
BE LAZY I DON'T LIKE IT.
>> LET'S MOVE ONTO PEOPLE WHO
DON'T NEED ANY MONETARY HELP,
THE NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS.
JOSH GORDON SUSPENDED BY THE
NFL BACK IN DECEMBER DUE TO
ANOTHER FAILED DRUG TEST,
ACCORDING TO MIKE REESE THE
PATRIOTS ARE GOING TO BE
GIVING HIM A SUPER BOWL RING
ANYWAY.
QUOTE FOR HIS CONTRIBUTIONS TO
THE TEAM'S SUCCESS OVER 11
GAMES AFTER HE WAS BROUGHT IN
FROM CLEVELAND.
EVEN THOUGH HE DIDN'T ACTUALLY
PLAY IN ANY OF THE PLAYOFF
GAMES INCLUDING THE SUPER
BOWL.
YOU MAY REMEMBER PATHS
RECEIVER WAS CENTS SUSPENDED
FOR THE FIRST GAMES OF THE TO
SOME SEASON AFTER VIOLATED THE
NFL POLICY AGAINST PERFORMANCE
ENHANCING DRUGS, HE WAS SUPER
BOWL MVP.
PUT A RING ON IT.
>> LIKE IT OR NOT.
>> EVERYTHING ABOUT IT, IF YOU
GET A TEAM YOU GET A RING.
I DON'T CARE HOW SMALL, HOW
LARGE THE CONTRIBUTION, IT IS
A TEAM SPORT.
I THINK THAT THIS USUAL OOH IS
MUTE.
I REALLY DON'T.
I DON'T SEE WHY IT WOULD BE
RISE TO EVEN THE SLIGHTEST
CONTROVERSY.
>> I THINK IT IS BIGGER THAN.
THAT WILL I THINK WE LIVE IN
THE DAY AND AGE WHERE THE NFL
OVERLOOKS DOMESTIC ABUSE,
LOOKS THE OTHER WAY THERE IS
ORGANIZATION THE PATRIOTS,
WHENEVER YOU STANDS UP
ORGANIZATION AND PATRIOTS IN
THE SAME SENTENCE?
WE SAY PATRIOTS AND CHEATERS.
THEY STAND BY THIS GUY WHO HAS
SUBSTANCE ABUSE ISSUE, MOST
ORGANIZATIONS CENTS WOULDN'T
DO THAT.
FURTHERMORE THEY DECIDED TO
GIFT HIM WITH THE RING.
I THINK THEY DE IS HER AFTER
HIGH FIVE FOR.
THAT ONCE AGAIN LOOK AT THE
CLIMATEMENT LOOK AT HOW THE
NFL TREAT EVERYTHING ELSE.
THEY DESERVE TO BE RECOGNIZED
FOR THIS.
>> ARE WE A WART G CHEATERS
NOW RINGS?
THAT'S HOW I SEE IT, YOU'RE
NOT SUPPOSED TO TAKE THIS
WHILE PERFORMING THIS JOB,
RIGHT, WHATEVER IT MAY BE.
YOU SEE, I WAS GIVING THIS
EXAMPLE EARLIER.
YOU DON'T EVEN SIGN YOUR CARD
IN GOLF AND YOU'RE OUT.
SO IF YOU HAVE BEEN TESTED AND
YOU TEST POSITIVE FOR PD IN
GOLF AND TENTS IS AND TALKING
SING ELSE ACTIVITIES SPORT
YOU'RE OUT.
THIS IS CHECK I HAVE SUPPORT.
OBVIOUSLY DIFFERENT.
BUT I THINK IT IS CENTS
CHEATING.
>> THIS IS COLLECTIVELY
BARGAINED THOUGH.
AND THE UNION TALKS TO THE
NFL.
THE UNION SAYS THIS IS THE
PUNISHMENT FOR DOING SOMETHING
LIKE THIS, HE SERVED HIS
PUNISHMENT.
HE SAT OUT FOUR GAMES, YOU CAN
FEEL, HE PLAYED IN THE GAMES,
HE WON, IN THE CASE OF JOSH
GORDON I FEEL LIKE.
>> THIS EVERY YEAR A SUPER
BOWL TEAM BOWL PLACE, GUYS NOT
THEREFORE THAT REASON WHY IT
BE INJURY, SUSPENSION, TRADE,
IT DOESN'T MEAN THEY WERE PART
THAT FAR, GIVE JOSH GORDON
PART OF HIS RING.
I KNOW HE DIDN'T PLAY IN THE
PLAYOFFS BUT GIVE HIM HIS
RING.
>> HE'LL HAVE AN ASTERISK NEXT
TO HIS NAME BUT IT WON'T BE AS
BIG AS IS THAT RING.
>> THE COMING UP HERE, MEGHAN
MARKLE HAS GOT A HOLLYWOOD BIG
WIG IN HER CORNER THESE DAYS.
GEORGE CLOONEY.
WE WILL TELL YOU WHAT HE IS
SAYING ABOUT HER RIGHT AFTER
THE BREAK.
STAY WITH US.
♪ We buy any car dot com ♪
♪ we buy any car dot com ♪
♪ ANY ANY ANY ANY ♪
Did you know trading in your car
at a dealer could cost
you money?
A recent study found consumers
who trade in their car
pay an average of $990
dollars more.
So don't trade in...
sell it....
to We Buy Any Car.
Learn more and get your free
online valuation
now at we buy any car dot com
♪ Find out how much your car is
worth at WeBuyAnyCar.com ♪
>> BASIC STATISTICS TELL US
THAT.
>> IF IN YOUR FINAL MOMENTS,
YOU SEE DEATH.
>> HELLO.
>> THINK NOT OF DEATH.
THINK OF THE LIVING.
>> AND KNOW THIS IT IS YOUR
SACRIFICE, WILL NOT HAVE BEEN
IN VEIN.
>> BACK ON FOX5 LIKE IT OR NOT
WITH GEORGE CLOONEY'S UPCOMING
HULU SERIES CATCH IT TWO,
WHILE PROMOTING IT SPOKE TO
HOO MAGAZINE TALKED ABOUT HIS
FRIENDS MEGHAN MARKLE YES THE
TWO OF THEM ARE FRIENDS, OSCAR
WINNER DEFENDE MEGAN HOW SHE
IS BEING TREATED BY SOME OF
THE PRESS AND THE PAPARAZZI,
QUOTE, SHE IS A WOMAN WHO IS P
MONTHS PREGNANT AND HAS BEEN
PURSUED AND VILIFIED AND
CHASED IN THE SAME WAY THAT
DIANA WAS, AND IT IS HISTORY
REPEATING IT SELF.
WE'VE SEEN HOW THAT ENDS.
GEORGE WAS OF COURSE REFERRING
TO PRINCESS DIANA'S FATAL
CRASH IN 199 P, IN PARIS, SO
WHAT DO WE THINK OF HIM
COMPARING THE TWO GUY LIKE IT
OR NOT?
>> I LIKE THIS A LOT.
NOTHING LIKE HAVING BIG
BROTHER STANDS UP FOR YOU,
CLOONEY LIKE HER BIG BROTHER
WITH REGARD TO MEGAN, YOU
WON'T SEE ME SHED ANY TEARS.
LOOK, SHE KNOWS WHAT SHE
SIGNED UP FOR.
WHEN YOU BECOME A RULE THE
SCRUTINY YOU FACE IS NO
SECRET.
SHE NEW SHE WOULD FACE THAT,
WHY SHOULD WE FEEL SORRY FOR
HER?
I WOULD ARGUE SHE PROBABLY HAS
MORE POSITIVE THINGS GOING ON
AS IS A ROYAL THAN A LOT MORE
NEGATIVE THINGS, DEAL WITH IT,
YOU'RE A ROYAL.
CAN'T THAN BAD.
>> YES, SHE CAME FROM
HOLLYWOOD.
>> YES, YOU AND MARINA ARE
VICIOUS.
>> LITTLE MORBID, THOUGH.
>> HOW?
>> SAYING IT MIGHT ENDS THE
SAME WAY.
PRINCESS DIANA DIED IN A
CRASH.
>> BECAUSE THE PAPARAZZI WERE
CHASING HER THROUGH TUNNELS,
AND I MEAN, THAT'S REALLY
MORBID THING TO SAY.
>> PRINCE HARRY AND EVERYBODY
ELSE.
>> BUT TO SAY IT MIGHT END, WE
SAW HOW THAT ONE ENDED IS
FOREBODING AND VERY MORBID AND
SCARY.
I DIDN'T LIKE THAT.
LIKE THE IDEA THAT SHE IS
GOING TO DIE YOUNG, I DIDN'T
LIKE THE IDEA OF THAT.
>> I DO THINK SHE DESERVES A
LITTLE SYMPATHY.
I DON'T KNOW YOU KNOW WHAT IT
IS LIKE TO BE A ROYAL UNTIL
YOU'RE A ROYAL.
LIKE THE PRESIDENCY I DON'T
KNOW YOU KNOW WHAT THE
PRESIDENT IS UNTIL YOU'VE A
PRESIDENT.
>> THEN DON'T RUN FOR IT.
>> OH, DON'T FALL IN LOVE.
>> OH, SURE IT IS LOVE.
>> OH.
>> THE CONTROL ROOM, WITH
ANOTHER BIG HOLLYWOOD TALKER.
>> I LOVE MARINE, A I LOVE
DOING ROYAL STORIES WHEN
MARINA IS ON, SO MUCH.
BUT YOU GUYS DID YOU WATCH THE
CROWN?
>> YES.
>> NO.
>> OH, MY, FIRST OF ALL,
PLEASE WATCH THE CROWN.
IT IS GREAT.
>> NO.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU CAN'T WATCH THE CROWN?
>> NO.
>> I LIKE MRS. CENTS MAZEL.
>> YOU CAN'T WATCH THE CROWN?
>> WHAT I LIKE ABOUT THE CROWN
>> I LIKE MRS. CENTS MAZEL.
IT, GIVES YOU SORT OF AN
>> WHAT I LIKE ABOUT THE CROWN
INSIGHT INTO THE OTHER SIDE.
IT, GIVES YOU SORT OF AN
YOU KNOW, AGAIN, I AGREE WITH
INSIGHT INTO THE OTHER SIDE.
A GUY BOO HOO ROYALS, BUT SORT
YOU KNOW, AGAIN, I AGREE WITH
OF GIVES YOU INSIGHT INTO WHAT
A GUY BOO HOO ROYALS, BUT SORT
THEY GO THROUGH.
OF GIVES YOU INSIGHT INTO WHAT
BUT SWITCHING GEARS
THEY GO THROUGH.
COMPLETELY, I SAW THE STORY
BUT SWITCHING GEARS
TODAY.
COMPLETELY, I SAW THE STORY
I HAD TO DO IT.
TODAY.
>> SO YOU GUYS KNOW I WAS
I HAD TO DO IT.
CENTS AT E FOR LONG TIME,
>> SO YOU GUYS KNOW I WAS
PEOPLE ALWAYS ASK ME OH, WHO,
CENTS AT E FOR LONG TIME,
WHO IS THE BEST CELEBRITY YOU
PEOPLE ALWAYS ASK ME OH, WHO,
EVER MET?
WHO IS THE BEST CELEBRITY YOU
I THINK YOU GUYS WOULD BE REAL
EVER MET?
SURPRISED IT IS BRETT
I THINK YOU GUYS WOULD BE REAL
MICHAELS.
SURPRISED IT IS BRETT
HE IS LIKE MY LEAD SINGER
MICHAELS.
POISON THE BEST CELEBRITY
HE IS LIKE MY LEAD SINGER
NUMBER ONE I MET IN MY LIFE
POISON THE BEST CELEBRITY
REALLY WELL SPOKEN, HE'S
NUMBER ONE I MET IN MY LIFE
REALLY POLITE.
REALLY WELL SPOKEN, HE'S
HE'S REALLY NICE, VERY SWEET,
REALLY POLITE.
WAS GREAT, I SPENT TIME AND
HE'S REALLY NICE, VERY SWEET,
INTERVIEWED HIM YEARS AGO.
WAS GREAT, I SPENT TIME AND
HIS DAUGHTERS IN THE NEW
INTERVIEWED HIM YEARS AGO.
SPORTS ILLUSTRATED ISSUE
HIS DAUGHTERS IN THE NEW
MAKING A LOT OF WAVES.
SPORTS ILLUSTRATED ISSUE
AND THEY ASKED HIM ABOUT THIS.
MAKING A LOT OF WAVES.
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY SHE IS
AND THEY ASKED HIM ABOUT THIS.
POSTED THIS BIKINI, AND
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY SHE IS
ANOTHER PHOTO I DECIDED NOT TO
POSTED THIS BIKINI, AND
SHOW BECAUSE IT IS KIND OF OUT
ANOTHER PHOTO I DECIDED NOT TO
THERE.
SHOW BECAUSE IT IS KIND OF OUT
AND IT IS A BIG DEAL TO BE IN
THERE.
THE SPORTS ILLUSTRATED ISSUE.
AND IT IS A BIG DEAL TO BE IN
IT IS HIS DAUGHTER THOUGH KIND
THE SPORTS ILLUSTRATED ISSUE.
OF COMING FULL CIRCLE RIGHT
IT IS HIS DAUGHTER THOUGH KIND
BECAUSE HE WAS CENTS THIS
OF COMING FULL CIRCLE RIGHT
CRAZY PARTIER BACK IN THE 80S,
BECAUSE HE WAS CENTS THIS
HE ADMITS YES IT IS FAKE
CRAZY PARTIER BACK IN THE 80S,
COMING FULL CIRCLE HERE.
HE ADMITS YES IT IS FAKE
BLEW WOULD A DAD SAY,'S DAD OF
COMING FULL CIRCLE HERE.
TWO DAUGHTERS, WHAT WOULD A
BLEW WOULD A DAD SAY,'S DAD OF
DAD SAY ABOUT THIS?
TWO DAUGHTERS, WHAT WOULD A
HE SAID HE'S PROUD OF HER.
DAD SAY ABOUT THIS?
HE'S PROUD AND I THINK BECAUSE
HE SAID HE'S PROUD OF HER.
SOME PEOPLE WERE SURPRISED
HE'S PROUD AND I THINK BECAUSE
ABOUT THAT BECAUSE HE'S
SOME PEOPLE WERE SURPRISED
EXPERIENCED IT, HE'S BEEN ON
ABOUT THAT BECAUSE HE'S
THE OTHER SIDE EVERY THINGS
EXPERIENCED IT, HE'S BEEN ON
NOW HIS DAUGHTERS POSE IN THE
THE OTHER SIDE EVERY THINGS
SPORT ILLUSTRATED BUT HE'S IN
NOW HIS DAUGHTERS POSE IN THE
SUPPORT OF T HE'S LIKE I'VE
SPORT ILLUSTRATED BUT HE'S IN
RAISED MY DAUGHTERS RIGHT.
SUPPORT OF T HE'S LIKE I'VE
I THINK THEY KNOW.
RAISED MY DAUGHTERS RIGHT.
I JUST KIND OF WANT TO KNOW
I THINK THEY KNOW.
WHAT YOU GUYS THINK ABOUT
I JUST KIND OF WANT TO KNOW
THIS, LIKE IT OR NOT?
WHAT YOU GUYS THINK ABOUT
>> NOPE.
THIS, LIKE IT OR NOT?
NOPE.
>> NOPE.
GRANTED I'M NOT BRETT
NOPE.
MICHAELS.
GRANTED I'M NOT BRETT
I HAD MY FUN, BUT DIDN'T ENDS
MICHAELS.
UP ON THE GRAM.
I HAD MY FUN, BUT DIDN'T ENDS
AND I'M HOPING MY DAUGHTER
UP ON THE GRAM.
DOESN'T EITHER IN THE PICTURES
AND I'M HOPING MY DAUGHTER
LIKE THAT, I JUST DON'T.
DOESN'T EITHER IN THE PICTURES
>> SHE'S A HOT GIRL.
LIKE THAT, I JUST DON'T.
>> YES.
>> SHE'S A HOT GIRL.
>> YOUR DAUGHTER WILL BE ON
>> YES.
THE GRAM LIKE THAT, SORRY,
>> YOUR DAUGHTER WILL BE ON
GRAM.
THE GRAM LIKE THAT, SORRY,
>> I DON'T KNOW.
GRAM.
>> ONCE SHE TURNS 18, RIGHT,
>> I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I MEAN --
>> ONCE SHE TURNS 18, RIGHT,
>> SHE CAN DO WHATEVER SHE
BUT I MEAN --
WANTS.
>> SHE CAN DO WHATEVER SHE
YOU KNOW, NOT DICTATORSHIP.
WANTS.
>> NO, THERE IS NOTHING --
YOU KNOW, NOT DICTATORSHIP.
>> BRIT'S DAD, BRIT, BRITNEY
>> NO, THERE IS NOTHING --
SPEARS, NOT BRIT MC HENRY.
>> BRIT'S DAD, BRIT, BRITNEY
AND PROBABLY BEYONCE'S DAD HAD
SPEARS, NOT BRIT MC HENRY.
T DEAL WITH THE SAME THING.
AND PROBABLY BEYONCE'S DAD HAD
SO WHAT DO YOU GUYS
There's the same old
way to get smooth,
And then there's New
Fructis Sleek Shot.
Our first
in-shower styler.
Infused with plant protein.
Just mix a shot with shampoo.
And power up with lather.
5x smoother hair.
Half the time.
It does the work for you,
So you can skip the flat iron.
Out with the old,
And in with
the smooth.
New Fructis Sleek Shot
In-Shower Styler.
By Garnier, naturally.