MEANTIME MORE NEWS AND MORE
WEATHER STARTING FOR YOU RIGHT
NOW.
>> RIGHT NOW AT 11:00, TRACKING
THE STORM.
>> WE ARE TRACKING ANOTHER
SYSTEM.
>> WE'RE TAKING YOU STEP BY STEP
THROUGH THIS WINTER STORM
APPROACHING IN JUST HOURS.
>> OUR TEAM COVERAGE CONTINUES
WITH PREPARATIONS FOR THE STORM.
WHY SOME ROAD CREWS ARE ACTUALLY
ENCOURAGED BY SUE'S FORECAST.
>>  PLUS, A BATHROOM DEBATE.
AND A FIGHT TORE STUDENT RIGHTS
GOES VIE AL.
HOW VIRGINIA ENDED UP BACK IN
THE NATIONAL SPOTLIGHT.
YOUR NEWS STARTS NOW.
>
>>>.
>> WE'RE GONNA BEGIN TONIGHT
WITH WINTER WEATHER WATCH FOR
MUCH OF THE DC REGION.
SNOW, SLEET, FREEZING RAIN ALL
ON THE MENU AND WINTER MIX COULD
BE NASTY ESPECIALLY DURING THE
MORNING COMMUTE.
>>  PROMPTED JUST ABOUT EVERY
SCHOOL DISTRICT TO CANCEL CLASS
TOMORROW ALONG WITH FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT.
ALL CLOSURES LISTED AT THE
BOTTOM OF YOUR SCREEN.
FOR NOW, GET RIGHT TO SUE PAL
CAN WITH BREAKDOWN WHEN THE
FIRST FLAKES START FALL.
>> HI THERE, ANYTIME BETWEEN 4
AND 6 IN THE MORNING HERE AROUND
THE BELTWAY.
YEAH, IT'S MORNING SNOW AND
MESSY ICY MIX TOMORROW
AFTERNOON.
UNFORTUNATELY THIS DOES NOT STAY
ALL SNOW WHICH WOULD BE THE
BETTER SCENARIO.
IT'S EASIER TO GET RID OF.
ICE CAUSES SO MANY PROBLEMS.
IT DOES LOOK LIKE WE ARE GOING
TO SEE THE CHANGE OVER AS WE
START WITH SNOW THAT WE NOW SEE
SHOWING UP ESPECIALLY SOUTH OF
INTERSTATE 64.
THAT WILL CONTINUE TO SPREAD
FROM SOUTHWEST TO NORTHEAST OVER
OUR AREA.
BY THE TIME YOU WAKE UP TOMORROW
MORNING BY SUN ADVISE YOU WILL
SEE SNOW OUTSIDE.
STARTING TO PUSH UP.
DO NOT EXPECT MUCH ACCUMULATION
FOR SOUTHERN VIRGINIA.
START WITH A LITTLE BIT, QUICKLY
CHANGE OVER DOWN THERE.
QUITE A SPRAWLING SYSTEM TO THE
PLAINS ACROSS ST. LOUIS AND
CINCINNATI TO MID ATLANTIC,
DEALING WITH IT FOR MANY HOURS
TOMORROW.
DID HAVE TO TAKE SNOW TOTALS
DOWN A LITTLE BIT TODAY BASED ON
MODEL OUTPUT AND FASTER CHANGE
OVER TO SLEET AND FREEZING RAIN.
STILL GOING WITH THREE TO FOUR
FIVES.
COULD BE CLOSER TO THREE INCHES
WITH SNOW.
CHANGE OVER SOMETIE IN THE
LIGHT MORNING.
OUT HERE CHANGE OVER A LITTLE
LATER, COULD GET A RATE OF SNOW
ONE INCH PER HOUR FEW HOURS IN
THE MORNING GET YOUR PILE UP.
UNFORTUNATELY ALL OF OUR AREA,
THIS MAY END, EGGS ING SRI IN
NORTHERN AND WESTERN SUBURB
EVERYBODY WEST OF 95 TO WATCH
FOR POTENTIAL FOR SIGNIFICANT
ICING AS THE TEMPERATURE BEGINS
WITH -- TEMPERATURE ALOFT BEGINS
TO RISE AND CHANGES SNOW OVER TO
COMBINATION OF SLEET AND
FREEZING RAIN.
COULD A QUARTER-INCH OF ICE BE
POSSIBLE IN SOME OF THESE AREAS
WE THINK THAT IS.
MAY OCCUR EARLY IN THE AFTERNOON
AND CONTINUE UNTIL THE TIME OF
EVENING RUSH HOUR.
SGLA WRAP UP 8 A.M. 30 DEGREES
IT'S SNOWING.
NOON HOUR, 32, MIXING ACROSS
MUCH OF THE AREA MAYBE NORTHERN
MARYLAND NOT QUITE YET OR
WESTERN MARYLAND.
FOUR O'CLOCK RAIN HERE IN DC.
POSSIBLY STILL FREEZING RAIN IN
FAR NORTHERN AND WESTERN
SUBURBS.
MUCH MORE TO COME INCLUDING HOUR
BY HOUR FUTURE CAST JUST AHEAD,
SARAH.
>> CREW US ALREADY HIT THE ROADS
LAYING SAND SALT AND BRINE.
NOW LITERALLY STANDING BY
WAITING TO WORK ON THOUSANDS OF
MILES OF ROADWAY.
TEAM COVERAGE OF APPROACHING
WINTER STORM CONTINUES.
LAUREN DEMARCO JOINS US LIVE
WITH THE LATEST OUT THERE.
LAUREN.
>> SIR REMARKS IT'S INCREDIBLE
TO WATCH THESE GUYS DO THEIR
WORK, FILLING UP TRUCK AFTER
TRUCK WITH SALT AND SAND.
THEY ARE READING OUT TO
INTERSTATES FROM SALT DOME IN
FAIRFAX AND ASKING FOR HELP FROM
THE PUBLIC TOMORROW WHEN ALL
THIS WET STUFF STARTS COMING
DOWN.
>>> IF EVERYBODY STAYS HOME,
HANGOUT, WATCH CHANNEL FIVE, IT
WOULD BE GREAT FOR US.
>> STAY HOME.
STAY HOME.
>>  IT'S GONNA BE PRETTY NASTY
THROUGHOUT THE DAY TOMORROW AND
INTO TOMORROW NIGHT'S RUSH.
REALLY ASKING THE FOLKS TO STAY
OFF THE ROAD IFS AT ALL
POSSIBLE.
>> UNIFIED MESSAGE FROM
TRANSPORTATION AND HIGHWAY
OFFICIALS IN VIRGINIA, MARYLAND
AND THE DISTRICT.
>> FOR FOLKS THAT DO VENTURE
OUT, I DON'T KNOW WHY THEY WOULD
DO THAT, WE WANT THEM TO
OBVIOUSLY FALL BEHIND OUR
SNOWPLOWS.
>> THOUSANDS OF PLOWS AND SALT
TRUCKS DEPLOYED ACROSS OR
RENALING YORK LOADING UP AND
GETTING IN PLACE OVERNIGT.
PREPARATIONS ACTUALLY BEGAN OVER
THE PAST FEW DAYS CREWS
PRETREATING HIGHWAYS LOCAL ROADS
KNOWN TROUBLE SPOTS WITH LIQUID
BRINE.
OFFICIALS ENCOURAGED BY THE
FORECAST.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE COMING IN AS
SNOW FROM WHAT WE'RE HEARING
BEAUTIFUL IN TERMS OF
INTERACTING WITH THE BRINE.
>>  WE'RE GONNA HAVE 3,000
TRUCKS OUT STARTING OVERNIGHT TO
BE ABLE TO PUSH THE SNOW OUT OF
THE WAY AS YOU SEE.
STARTING TO ROLL THROUGH HERE.
>> ANYONE WHO HAS TO BE OUT IS
URGED TO PREPARE WITH EMERGENCY
SUPPLY KIT, CHARGED CELL PHONE
AND FULL TANK OF GAS.
PLENTY OF PEOPLE HEEDING THAT
ADVICE AT COSTCO'S POPULAR GAS
STATION IN FAIRFAX.
>> IT'S CRAZY.
IT'S ALWAYS BUSY HERE.
BUT TODAY IS EXTREMELY BUSY.
PEOPLE THINK THAT THE SKY IS
GOING TO FALL.
>> I THINK PEOPLE DON'T WANT TO
GET STUCK.
>> OVER AT HOME DEPOT PEOPLE
STOCKING UP ON ICE MELT, SHOVELS
AND OTHER USUAL NECESSITIES.
>>  WHAT I'M CONCERNED ABOUT HOW
MUCH SNOW WE'RE GOING TO GET.
>> THREE BOYS WE'RE GOING TO BE
WORKING.
>> BETWEEN SNOW, FREEZING RAIN
OR AT LEAST FREEZING
PRECIPITATION AND POSSIBLY SOME
ICE, EXPECTED TO IMPACT THE NEXT
THREE RUSH HOURS.
VDOT TOLD ME TONIGHT BECAUSE
THIS IS STARTING WITH SNOW AND
EXPECTING TO ACCUMULATE THEY
WILL BE IN SUBDIVISIONS AS WELL.
THEY AND ALL AREA OFFICIALS
ASKING THAT IN YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD
TRY TO PARK IN A DRIVEWAY OR ALL
ON ONE SIDE OF THE ROAD THAT WAY
THE PLOWS HAVE EASIER TIME
GETTING BY.
BACK TO YOU IN THE STUDIO.
>> SEVERAL AREA SCHOOLS ALREADY
OUT OF SNOW DAYS.
IN FACT, TOMORROW SEND MORE
SCHOOLS OVER DAY BUDGETS FOR
WEATHER CANCELLATION.
MONTGOMERY COUNTY USED TWO
MAKEUP DAYS ALREADY.
HOWARD COUNTY USED FOUR MAKEUP
DAYS.
IF THEY HAVE TO MISS ANY MORE
SCHOOL DISTRICT APPEAL TO STATE
BOARD OF EDUCATION AND ASK FOR
FORGIVENESS OR MAKE ADJUSTMENTS
TO SCHOOL CAR DAL.
>> FAIRFAX, PRINCE WILLIAM
LOUDOUN ALL HAVE DAYS TO SPARE.
>> STORM FORCING METRO TO ADJUST
BUS AND RAIL SERVICE.
TRAINS RUN EVERY 12 MINUTES
ALLOWING WORKERS TO DERICE THE
TRACKS.
SCHEDULE COULD CHANGE AS
SCHEDULE UNFOLDS.
METROBUS OPERATE UNDER SEVERE
SNOW SERVICE PLANS.
THAT MEANS BUS PROS VIED LIMITED
SERVICE ON MAJOR ROADWAYS ONLY.
METRO ACCESS ONLY PROVIDE RETURN
TRIPS HOME FOR CUSTOMERS BETWEEN
4:00 A.M. AND 7 P.M.
ALL OTHER TRIPS CANCELLED.
YOU CAN TRACK THE WEATHER 24-7
ON "FOX5" WEATHER APP.
LATEST ON "FOX5" MORNING
BEGINNING AT 4:00 A.M.
>> ANOTHER LIFE LOST IN WHAT IS
CALLED THE HIGHWAY OF DEATH.
JUAN CASTILLO KILLED LAST NIGHT
INDIAN HEAD HIGHWAY ROUTE 210 IN
ACCOKEEK.
SIMILAR TO A CRASH THAT KILLED
THREE CHILDREN ON SAME ROAD BACK
IN DECEMBER.
"FOX5" LINDSAY WATTS SPOKE WITH
CASTILLO'S HEARTBROKEN FAMILY.
LINDSAY JUS SHAWN IF IN THAT
CRASH LAST NIGHT AND THE ONE IN
DECEMBER, DRIVERS WERE STOPPED
AT RED LIGHT HERE ON INDIAN HEAD
HIGHWAY WHEN ANOTHER VEHICLE
CAME BARRELLING UP FROM BEHIND
AND CRASHED.
THE EFFORTS TO MAKE INDIAN HEAD
HIGHWAY SAFER, BUT POLICE SAY IT
ALSO FALLS ON DRIVERS TO PAY
ATTENTION WHEN THEY ARE BEHIND
THE WHEEL.
>>> I FEEL HE'S MY DADDY.
I LOVE HIM SO MUCH AND I'M GOING
TO MISS HIM.
>> JUAN MENDEZ CASTILLOS WITH A
FATHER AND GRANDFATHER.
HE WAS DRIVING WITH FAMILY
MEMBER MONDAY NIGHT ABOUT SIX
MILES FROM HIS HOME IN WALDORF.
>> MY BROTHER-IN-LAW IS DRIVING
THE CAR.
>>  THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED TO
THAT VEHICLE, A FORD ESCAPE.
ACCORDING TO POLICE, IT WAS
STOPPED AT A RED LIGHT ON INDIAN
HEAD HIGHWAY AT BERRY ROAD IN
ACCOKEEK.
INVESTIGATORS SAY A FEMALE
DRIVER DIDN'T STOP, PLOWING INTO
THE ESCAPE.
MENDEZ CASTILLO DIED AT THE HOP.
FAMILY ONLY RECENTLY MOVED FROM
VIRGINIA ALL WELL AWAY OF 210'S
NOTORIETY.
HE SAW NEWS COVERAGE OF
HORRIFYING CRASH THAT CLAIMED
THE LIFE OF THREE CHILDREN.
>> WHEN I SAW THE ACCIDENT BACK
ON DECEMBER, HE SAID OH, MY GOD,
EVERYBODY BE CAREFUL ON THAT
STREET IT'S DANGERER.
>> PRINCE GEORGE'S COUNTY HAVE
RAMPED UP ENFORCE THE ON THE
HIGHWAY, ISSUING 3700 CITATIONS
IN JUST THE LAST MONTH AND A
HALF.
THERE WAS A DUI CHECKPOINT
EARLIER THIS MONTH.
COUNTY WORKING TO GET STATE
FUNDING TO IMPROVE THE ROAD.
BILL ADVANCING IN ANNAPOLIS
WOULD ADD UP TO 7 ROVING SPEED .
RIGHT NOW THERE'S ONLY ONE
PERMANENT SPEED CAMERA ON 210.
>> I THINK THEY'RE DOING
EVERYTHING I CAN THINK OF.
>> THE ROAD IS UP A HAZARD
THERE'S COMMUNITY GROUP DEVOTED
TO MAKING IT SAFER.
RON WEISS IS PART OF THAT.
>> WE THINK OF 210 AS OUR MAIN
STREET AND IT'S JUST NOT A GOOD
FEELING WHEN YOU GO OUT ON YOUR
MAIN STREET AND WORRYING ABOUT
B
BEING KILLED.
>> HE SAID RECENT CRASHES
PREVENTABLE AND UP TO DRIVERS TO
TAKE BACK CONTROL.
>> BACK HERE LIVE NOW, THE CRASH
LAST NIGHT IS STILL UNDER
INVESTIGATION.
POLICE ARE TRYING TO FIND OUT
WHY THAT FEMALE DRIVER DIDN'T
STOP.
BACK TO YOU.
>> NEW AT 11 NOW, VIRGINIA HOUSE
DEMOCRATS TODAY SAID THEY ARE
TREATING THE SEXUAL ASSAULT
ALLEGATIONS AGAINST LUFT GOLF
JUSTIN FAIRFAX SERIOUSLY.
IN A STATEMENT THEY SAID WE
RESPECT ALL SURVIVORS AND
BELIEVE THEY SHOULD BE FULLY
HEARD.
IN RESPONSE, THE ATTORNEY FOR
ACCUSERS MEREDITH WATSON SAID
APPARENTLY THE VIRGINIA HOUSE
DEMOCRATIC CAUCUS BELIEVE THAT
IS COURAGEOUS VICTIMS OF RAPE
NEED TO BE HEARD, JUST NOT BY
THEM.
MS. WATSON IS COUNTING ON
GENERAL ASSEMBLY TO DO THE RIGHT
THING AND HOLD HEARINGS NOW.
>> GUNMAN SHOT UP A CAR IN
POPULAR ICE ARENA DISTRICT STILL
ON THE RUN TONIGHT.
SHOOTING HAPPENED THIS AFTERNOON
FORD DUE FONT ICE ARENA
SOUTHEAST.
TWO MEN AND CHILD SHOT.
ONE CHIT DULL AND OTHER TWO
EXPECTED TO BE OK.
>> LOOKING FOR SILVER HYUNDAI
MIGHT BE CONNECT.
>> GOOD NEWS SOUTHEAST DC FAMILY
YOU RELIEN0 THE ICE RAINA.
MUCH-NEEDED FACELIFT THANKS TO
DEAL REACHED BETWEEN MAYOR
BOWSER AND FRIENDS OF DUPONT
RCE A REN IN A NOPE PROFIT THAT
RUNS THAT RINK.
IF THE GROUP RAISES 3 MILLION OF
THE 30 MILLION DOLLAR EXPANSION
BUDGET BY NEXT FEBRUARY THEY
WILL BEGIN THE PROJECT.
>> WASHINGTON NATIONALS FIRST
FULL SQUAD SPRING TRAINING WORK
OUT.
BRIGHTS HARPER IS NOT ON THE
FIELD.
HE'S FREE AGENT RIGHT NOW AND
STILL NOT SIGNED WITH A TEAM.
>>  SOME MONTGOMERY COUNTY HIGH
SCHOOL STUDENTS ENCOURAGING
OTHER STUDENTS TO USE A RACIAL
SLUR AND OF COURSE IT'S STIRRING
CONTROVERSY.
>> EVAN LAMB EARTH WORKING ON
THE STORY DON'T.
>>  PARENTS STUDENT AND SCHOOL
LEADER IT'S MET TO TALK ABOUT
SOLUTIONS WHAT THE PRINCIPAL
CALLED RACIST ACT.
MORE COMING UP.
>> EACH OF US HAVE GIFTS THAT
EXPRESS THEMSELVES IN DIFFERENT
WAYS.
>>  FORMER PRESIDENT OBAMA IS
HEADING UP ALLIANCE TO SUPPORT
YOUNG MEN OF COLOR.
WE'LL TAKE YOU TO OAKLAND FOR
THE FIRST -- FOR THE FIRST MY
BROTHERS KEEPER SUMMIT.
>>> AND COMING UP TONIGHT ON
FINAL 5.
BERNIE SANDERS BACK FOR
DEMOCRATIC PRIMARY.
WHAT DOES HIS ANNOUNCEMENT MEAN
FOR THE PRESIDENTIAL RACE AND
WHAT WILL BE DIFFERENT FROM HIS
2016 CAMPAIGN?  CATCH "THE FINAL
FIVE" TONIGHT AT 11:30.
.
>>> ♪ ♪
>>> SOME STUDENTS HAVE TULLY
BEEN SHARING A CARD THAT GIVES
OTHER STUDENTS A PASS TO USE THE
N-WORD.
TONIGHT, ADMINISTRATORS AND
PARENTS MET TO TALK ABOUT
SOLUTIONS.
FOX5'S EVAN LAMBERT HERE WITH
THE LATEST.
>>REPORTER:  SCHOOL OCCASIONS
FOUND THE PASSES ON FEBRUARY 8TH
AT WINSTON CHURCHILL HIGH SCHOOL
IN POTOMAC MARYLAND.
TONIGHT, CONCERNED PARENTS AND
STUDENTS WANTED TO HEAR WHAT THE
SCHOOL'S PLAN WAS TO DISCOURAGE
RACIST LANGUAGE AND ACTS.
THISES WHAT THE PASSES LOOKED
LIKE.
THEY'RE BASED ON A MEME OF A
WILLY WONKA GOLDEN TICKET.
HOLDER, ACCORDING TO THE TICKET,
GETS PERMISSION TO USE THE
N-WORD.
TONIGHT SCHOOL OFFICIALS SAID
THEY COME UP WITH A PLAN ROLLED
OUT IN PHASES TO TURN THE
EPISODE INTO TEACHABLE MOMENT.
STUDENTS WOULD BE EDUCATED ABOUT
RACISM AND EQUAL TEE.
GROUP OF ABOUT 40 STUDENT
LEADERS ALREADY MET ABOUT HOW
THEY CAN TALK TO OTHER STUDENTS.
PARENTS THOUGHT USING STUDENTS
OWN VOICES TO EDUCATE EACH OTHER
WOULD BE MOST EFFECTIVE.
>> ALL CAME HERE THINKING PLAN
IN PLAY.
A LOT OF BRAINSTORMING GOING ON,
WHICH IS GOOD.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, I THINK
IT'S GOING TO TAKE WAY MORE THAN
THAT.
PEER PRESSURE IS HUGE IN HIGH
SCHOOL.
USE THAT ARE GOOD AND HAVE
INFLUENCE THEIR PEERS AND YOU
HEAR IT IN SONG THAT DOESN'T
MEAN IT'S OK.
>> STARTS WITH THE KIDS, STARTS
WITH THE PARENTS.
STARTS WITH THE SCHOOL, THE
TEACHERS, EVERYBODY COLLECTIVELY
PLAY A ROLE IN MAKING A CHANGE.
>> BACK WHEN THE PASSES WERE
DISCOVERED PRINCIPAL CALLED
RACIST HATEFUL ACT THAT DOES NOT
REFLECT THE VALUES OF STUDENTS
DISCIPLINE WITHED CODE OF
CONDUCT.
>> JUSSIE SMOLLETT'S LAWYERS
INSIST THE EMPIRE ACTOR DID NOT
ORCHESTRATE ONLY ASSAULT DESPITE
SPECULATION HE PAID TWO MEN TO
ATTACK HIM ON CHICAGO STREET.
TWO BROTHERS INITIALLY
QUESTIONED AN RELEASED
REPORTEDLY TOLD POLICE SMOLLETT
PAID THEM AND SHE HERSED TO
CARRY OUT ASSAULT.
SAID SMOLLETT WAS UPSET WASN'T
ENOUGH ATTENTION TO THREATENING
LETTER RECEIVED.
FBI SEPARATE INVESTIGATION INTO
THAT LETTER.
BELIEVE HE MAY HAVE SENT TO
HIMSELF.
>> VIRGINIA SCHOOL DISTRICT
CONSIDERING A NEW PROPOSAL TO
ALLOW TRANSGENDER STUDENTS TO
USE RESTROOM OF THEIR CHOICE.
DOZENS TURNED OUT FOR HEARING IN
GLOUCESTER COUNT HE.
ALLOW TRANSGENDER TO USE THEIR
CHOICE AS LONG AS IDENTITY IS AT
LEAST SIX MONTHS.
REVERSE THE COUNTIES CURRENT
POLICY SUBJEC OF LAWSUIT SINCE
ADOPTED BACK IN 2014.
THAT PROPOSAL SAID STUDENTS
COULD ONLY USE THE RESTAURANT
THAT CORRESPONDED WITH THEIR SEX
AT BIRTH.
>> ALMOST LIKES LIKE THE REAL
DEAL BUT IT'S NOT.
FAKE MONEY, MAINLY $100 BILLS IS
MAKING ITS WAY AROUND NORTHERN
VIRGINIA.
BUT THERE ARE SOME EASY WAYS TO
SPOT THE COUNTERFEIT BILLS AND
VOID BECOMING A VICTIM OR AVOID
PASSING IT ALONG.
>> YOU CAN SEE ON THE
COUNTERFEIT BILL, IT SAYS FOR
MOTION PICTURE USE ONLY, A LOT
OF SECURITY FEATURES THROUGH
THIS LEGITIMATE HUNDRED DOLLAR
BILL, YOU CAN SEE THE DIFFERENCE
IN COLOR.
THERE'S DIFFERENT FEEL IN THE
TEXTURE.
>>  THE STAFFORD COUNTY
SHERIFF'S OFFICE THERE SAYING
THEY HAVE NO IDEA RIGHT NOW HOW
MANY FAKE BILLS ARE IN
CIRCULATION IN THE AREA.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, WE WILL HAVE SOME SNOW AND
MAYBE SOME SLEET, RAIN, ICE IN
CIRCULATION IN OUR AREA
TOMORROW.
>> THERE'S OUR FORECAST.
THANK YOU, SHAWN.
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYONE.
BEEN A LONG DAY.
>> YOU WISH.
>> [LAUGHTER].
>> SHOW YOU HOW CLOSE IT'S
GETTING.
FORTUNATELY FOR US WE GET TO GET
HOME BEFORE THIS STARTS.
IF YOU HAVE A MORNING COMMUTE
TOMORROW, I KNOW A LOT OF
SCHOOLS CANCELLED GOVERNMENT HAS
CANCELLED I'M GLAD IT.
SNOW FALLING INTENSELY.
VISIBILITY A PROBLEM.
ROADS BRINED AN TREATED IF WE DO
GET A BURST MODERATE TO HEAVY
SNOW THAT FALLS AT RIGHT OF INCH
PER HOUR, EVEN THREE OR FOUR
HOUR THAT IS COULD BE A REAL
PROBLEM.
TEMPERATURES ARE GOING TO
CONTINUE TO DROP.
WE'RE AT 38 DEGREES.
THERE WILL BE STICKAGE TOMORROW
MORNING.
NOT THE COLDEST NIGHT, SOMEWHAT
SLUSHY WET SNOW AS IT FALLS.
HEAVY WET SNOW.
SEE THIS PRIMARILY IN THE
MORNING HOURS AN CHANGE OVER
LATE MORNING TO NOON.
THAT TIMING OF THE CHANGE OVER
IS GOING TO BE CRUCIAL.
OVERNIGHT TEMPERATURES NEAR 30
TO ABOUT 32 DEGREES.
HERE'S OUR STORM TRACKER RADAR,
YOU CAN SEE WE DO SEE SNOW
TRYING TO EXPARTICIPATED
CERTAINLY ALOFT, NORTH OF 46
NOW.
HITTING THE GROUND DOWN THERE?
PROBABLY NOT JUST YET.
WE'VE GOT DRY AIR TO OVER COME
BRIEFLY.
MAKING STEADY PROGRESS,
SOUTHWEST TO NORTHEAST.
EXPECT IT IN BETWEEN 6 TO 7 IN
THE MORNING CROSSING THE
BELTWAY.
BIG STORM AS YOU KNOW.
IT HAD IMPACT FOR NEBRASKA FOR
KANSAS FOR OKLAHOMA FOR ST.
LOUIS.
PUSHING INTO CINCINNATI NOW AND
LEADING I THINK OF THAT ALL TURN
OVERED
ED OVER TO SNOW.
THAT'S WITH WE EXPECT TO SEE, 6
O'CLOCK SOUTHWEST NORTHEAST.
8 A.M. SEEING THE BLUE SHOWING
SNOW AROUND OUR AREA.
THIS WILL CONTINUE FOR A FEW
HOURS.
WATCH THIS.
THE PINK, AND OUR MODEL BRINGS
THAT IN RIGHT ABOUT 11 O'CLOCK.
THIS DID UPDATE JUST A LITTLE
WHILE AGO AND IT HOLDS THE SNOW
IN JUST A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
MAYBE THAT CHANGE OVER IS CLOSER
TO THE NOON HOUR.
BUT THIS IS WHERE WE START TO
SEE THE SLEET COMING IN, THE
LITTLE ICE PELLETS THAT
PARTICULAR ON YOUR WINDOW.
2 O'CLOCK DC LOOKS LIKE OVER TO
RAIN.
BIT OF SNOW IN NORTHEASTERN
MARYLAND.
ALL ICING AND SLEET AND FREEZING
RAIN BEGIN TO ACCUMULATE.
QUARTER-INCH OF ICE PROBLEM FOR
AREAS AS WORK THROUGH THE EARLY
PART OF AN NOOCHL AFTERNOON.
>>  LINGERING FREEZING RAIN,
ALWAYS IS.
WORRY ABOUT ACCUMULATION ON
TREES AND LIMBS COULD PRESENT
POWER OUTAGES AND CERTAINLY SOME
TRICKY TRAVEL IN THOSE AREAS.
HERE'S TEN O'CLOCK FUTURECAST.
MOSTLY RAIN AND BY THE TIME WE
GET TO THURSDAY MORNING IT'S 7
A.M., IT IS OUT OF HERE.
IF YOU HAVEN'T SEEN THIS BEFORE,
GENERALLY WE'RE GOING FOR THREE
TO FIVE INCH SNOWFALL AMOUNT
ESPECIALLY THROUGH THE METRO
AREA.
COULD BE CLOSER TO THREE INCH
AMOUNT IF CHANGE OVER HAPPENS
SOONER.
FIVE INCH AMOUNT IF CHANGE OVER
HAPPENS LATER.
HEAVIEST SNOW FIVE TO EIGHT INCH
IT'S OUT HERE ALSO A PROBLEM ICE
IN THE AFTERNOON, QUARTER-INCH
UT THERE, ONE TO THREE INCHES
SOUTH AN EAST FOR SOUTHERN
MARYLAND.
COMPARING MODELS PUTTING OUT
THERE.
YESTERDAY THIS MODEL BY
AGGRESSIVE WITH SNOW.
DID COME DOWN TODAY.
IT THIS IS STILL A PRETTY
SIGNIFICANT SNOW.
AMERICAN MODEL.
LAST THING I'LL SHOW YOU
EUROPEAN MODEL, STICKING WITH AN
A LESS IMPACTFUL SNOW PART OF
THE STORM BUT STILL CAN SEE THE
ICE IN THE AFTERNOON.
THIS IS TWO INFORM TO ABOUT SIX
INCHES AROUND THE AREA.
WE FEEL PRETTY GOOD THAT THOSE
NUMBERS GOING TO BE WHAT WE END
UP GETTING.
WITH HE KNOW IT'S GOING TO BE A
MESSY DAY REGARDLESS AND
THURSDAY, WE START TO MELT IT
OFF, 49 DEGREES.
FRIDAY, WE CONTINUE THE MELTING.
RAIN ON SATURDAY WITH A
TEMPERATURE OF 44.
WE COULD SEE THE RAIN LINGER
INTO THE FIRST PART OF SUNDAY,
BUT I THINK MOST OF THE DAY
SUNDAY IS GOING TO BE MILDER AND
EVENTUALLY PRETTY DRY AT 64
DEGREES.
MONDAY, SUNNY, TUESDAY ANOTHER
CHANCE OF RAIN/SNOW MIX THAT WE
HAVE TO KEEP AN EYE ON WITH
TEMPERATURE OF 47 ON TUESDAY.
WATCHING THAT ONE CLOSELY AND
YOU CAN CONTINUE TO MONITOR THAT
AS WELL AS ALL THE DEVELOPMENTS
AS WE WORK OUR WAY HOUR BY HOUR
THROUGH A TRICKY WEDNESDAY
AROUND HERE THAT COULD REALLY BE
PROBLEMATIC ON THE ROADS BY
DOWNLOADING THE "FOX5" WEATHER
APP.
SHAWN, BACK TO YOU.
>> SPACE THAT'S THE NEXT STEP
AND WE HAVE TO BE PREPARED.
>>  PRESIDENT TRUMP'S GOAL TO
ADD A SIXTH BRANCH TO THE
MILITARY A STEP CLOSE TORE
BECOMING REALITY.
TODAY HE SIGNED A DIRECTIVE TO
ESTABLISH THE SPACE FORCE F.
APPROVED BY CONGRESS THE BRANCH
WOOING ALLOWED -- EXCUSE ME,
WOULD ALLOW THE DEPARTMENT OF
DEFENSE TO HAENLD ALL SPACE
OPERATIONS.
>> FORMER PRESIDENT BARACK OBAMA
TURNING UP AT EVENT IN OAKLAND
CALIFORNIA.
JOINED BY BASKETBALL STAR STEPH
CURRY, JOHN LEGEND TO EMPOWER
YOUNG MEN OF COWL.
CALLED MBK RISING.
FORMER PRESIDENT STARTED MY
BROTHER'S KEEPER SEVERAL YEARS
BACK.
SO MUCH CAN BE ACCOMPLISHED
THROUGH MENTORSHIP.
>> I DID NOT GROW UP AND BECOME
THE PERSON I AM UNTIL I WAS LESS
FOCUSED ON ME AND I WAS MORE
FOCUSED ON HOW COULD I BE
USEFUL?  WHO COULD I HELP? .
>> MR. OBAMA SAYS BEING A
POSITIVE INFLUENCE ON SOMEONE
CAN BE BENEFICIAL TO YOU BECAUSE
IT ALSO GIVES YOU THE CONFIDENCE
WHEN THEY SUCCEED.
PAY IT FORWARD THING GOING ON
THERE.
>> I LIKE IT.
FLORIDA HOME TO ORANGES, HOME TO
DISNEY WORLD AND ALSO HOME TO
USUALLY BIZARRE NEWS.
>> STRAIGHT AHEAD SHOW YOU HOW
AN OFFICER --.
>>> ♪ ♪
PASS PASS
Here's your Buick sir.
Actually, that's my Buick.
Your Buick doesn't have a
roof rack!
This is my Buick.
How are we gonna fit in your
mom's Buick?
Easy.
I like that new Buick.
Me too.
I was actually talking about
that Buick.
I knew that.
Did you?
Buick's fresh new lineup is full
of surprises.
Get great deals on our
expectation-shattering lineup.
Pay no interest for 72 months
on most Buick models.
.
>>> OFFICER WAS ON PATROL WHEN
HE CAME ACROSS A HERD OF BILLY
GOATS.
HERDED THEM HOME.
KNOW
KNOCKED DOWN THE FENCE.
IN FLORIDA BY THE WAY.
WHATEVER
Do you think this is fun for me?
You think I'm having fun?
[Man on other line] It certainly
wasn't much fun to.....
Do you have eyes on the target?
Is it her?
[Man on other line] I can't tell
from this photos...
...I need better shots.
Thank you for flying
Turkish Airlines.
Taxi!
You waiting for someone?
No. Just... looking.