ON FURNITURE THAT'S
ALREADY MARKED DOWN!
WITH MORE STYLES
AND CUSTOM FABRICS
TO CHOOSE FROM.
CELEBRATE YOUR
INDEPENDENCE WITH
FURNITURE THAT
FITS YOU.
HAVERTYS
LIFE LOOKS GOOD
YOUR NEWS STARTS NOW.
WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH A LIVE
LOOK AT NATIONAL MALL.
TOMORROW PEOPLE WILL FILL THEM
ALL TO CELEBRATE THE 4th OF
JULY.
IT'S ALL CLEAR TONIGHT AND
WE'RE WATCHING FOR POPUP
STORMS THAT COULD PUT A DAMPER
ON HOLIDAY PLANS TOMORROW.
>>  SHE'S TRACK WHEN AND WHERE
THE STORMS COULD HIT AND YOU
KNOW WE'RE KIND OF USED TO
HOSPITAL TO 4th OF JULY AREN'T
WE.
>>> WE DO THIS EVERY YEAR.
WHAT'S THE HOLIDAY WITHOUT A
WEATHER CHALLENGE HERE
ESPECIALLY IN SUMMER.
WE'LL DO THAT TOMORROW.
SEVERAL ROUNDS OF POPUP
SHOWERS AND STORMS.
DEPENDING WHERE YOU ARE YOU
MAY NOT SEE HUTCH MUCH.
OTHER SPOTS MAY SEE A LOT.
STORMY DAY TOMORROW.
POX IS THERE FOR SHOWERS AND
STORMS TO FIRE UP.
SOME MAY BE SEVERE AND SOME
MAY BRING HEAVY RAIN.
THAT'S A LOT TO KEEP TRACK OF
FROM POOL PARTIES TO FIREWORKS
FESTIVITIES.
WE HAVE THE DAY OFF.
SHOWERS AND THUNDERSTORMS LAST
NIGHT WERE RELENTLESS.
SO IT WAS WONDERFUL TO NOT SEE
HUTCH AROUND THE METRO.
WE'LL STAY WAYET OVERNIGHT FEW
CLOUDS MUGGY AND MILD LOW OF
76, LOOK AGO HEAD TOMORROW
HEAT WAVE ROLLS ON AN WE'LL
SEE TEMPERATURES INTO 990s AND
HEAT INDEX IN UPPER 90s.
AS EARLY AS LUNCH HOUR SHOWERS
AND STORMS ARE EXPECTED TO
FIRE UP AND ONE OF THOSE DAYS
YOU MAY BE DODGING THEM.
HAVE A BACKUP PLAN IF ARE YOU
OUTDOORS.
THERE COULD BE FEW POST
POPEMENTS TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
MORNING FORECAST TEMPERATURES
MILE 80.
NEAR 9 THE 0 LUNCH HOUR AND
WATCHING FOR SHOWERS AND
THUNDERSTORMS.
INTO FIREWORKS TIME I THINK
MOST HEAVY HITTING ACTION WILL
BE OVER WITH.
SEVERE WEATHER BY 9:00 THERE
COULD BE LINGERING RAIN WE'LL
TALK MORE ABOUT THAT AND
FUTURE CAST COMING NUPT 7P DAY
FORECAST.
>>  NOW THOUGHT KNOW THE
FORECAST LET'S GET YOU CAUGHT
UP ON EVERYTHING I NEED TO
KNOW ABOUT EVENTS IN DISTRICT.
EVENTS IN D.C. START BEFORE
NOON WITH NATIONAL
INDEPENDENCE DAY PARADE ON
CONSTITUTION AVENUE NORTHWEST.
GATES OPEN AT 3 WITH:30 P.M.
FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP SALUTE FOR
AMERICA.
LINCOLN MEMORIAL.
ANNUAL CAPITOL FOURTH GETS
UNDERWAY WEST LAWN OF CAPITAL
8 TOMORROW NIXINGTS BIG
FIREWORKS DISPLAY EXPECTED TO
BEGIN AFTER 9 PAEX.
>>  NOW IN ADDITION TO MASSIVE
FIREWORKS DISPLAY AND CONCERT
NEW THIS YEAR PRESIDENT TRUMP
SALUTE TO AMERICA INCLUDING
TANKS, MILITARY PLAY-OVER AND
HEFTY PRICE TAG SOME SAY IS
OUT RAGE US AND OTHERS SAY IT
MONEY WELL SPENT.
"FOX5" JOSH ROSENTHAL IS LIVE
NEAR LINCOLN MEMORIAL WITH THE
LATEST, HEY, JOSH.
>>  HEY, SHAWRNGS YOU KNOW
WE'RE LESS THAN 24 HOURS AWAY.
AS YOU CAN SEE THIS YEAR'S
FOUVRJ JULY WILL BE DIFFERENT
THAN YEARS PAST.
IN MY MIND THIS IT GREAT.
>>  CONGRESS DON'T GET THEIR
ACT TOGETHER AND WANT TO WASTE
ON THEIR PET PROJECTS WHY NOT
HAVE SOMETHING TO CELEBRATE
US.
>> EVERYONE IS NOT QUITE SO
PLEASED.
HERE'S THE DEAL WASHINGTON
POSTS REPORTED NATIONAL PARK
SERVICES DIVERTING 2.59
MILLION TO DIVERT COSTS.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN SPENT ON
PARKS ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND
POTHOLES ON CERTAIN ROAD RICK
GW PARKWAY.
THERE'S A 1 IS 2 BILLION
BACKLOG.
MAINTENANCE NEEDS THE PARK
SERVICE IS ALREADY STRUGGLING
TO PATLE.
>>  THEY WANT TO PROTECT
NATIONAL PARKS AND PROVIDE
MONEY NECESSARY TO ADDRESS
BACKLOG OF PARK SERVICE AND
THEN THEY USE VALUABLE DOLLARS
FROM PARK VISITORS TO PAY FOR
THIS SPECTACLE.
>>  AND I REACHED OUT TO THE
NATIONAL PARK SERVICE WITH A
LOT OF QUESTIONS AND THEY
DEPOSIT ANSWER ANY.
THEY SENT A STATEMENT
DEPARTMENT OF INTERIOR IS
COMMITTED TO PROVIDING
AMERICAN PEOPLE FANTASTIC
CELEBRATION OF NATION'S
BIRTHDAY AND DOING SO
CONSISTENT WITH THE
DEPARTMENT'S MISSION AND
HISTORICAL PRACTICES.
I WANT TO MENTION WE DON'T
HAVE A FINAL TOTAL PRICE FAING
TAG FOR THE EVENT.
HOWEVER SOME OF THE STUFF YOU
SEE, FOR INSTANCE, EXTRA FOYER
WORKS HAVE BEEN DONATESED BACK
TO YOU.
>>  AND PRESIDENT SALUTE TO
AMERICA TOMORROW IS EXPECTED
TO ATTRACT PROTESTERS.
MEMBERS OF CODE PINK PLAN TO
DEM SCAIT.
THE EVENT IS TURN INTO
MILITARY STIFLE FORCE AND DOES
NOT REPRESENT TRUE MEANING OF
INDEPENDENCE DAY.
THEY WANTED TO FLY BADE TRUMP
BALLOON WE HAVE SEEN IN LONDON
AND OTHER PARTS OF EUROPE.
THE NATIONAL PARK SERVICE DEP
EYED THE REQUEST.
EVEN FT. BALLOON CANNOT NATURE
GROUP WILL TAKE A STAND.
>> WE DO THINK IT'S IMPORTANT
TO OPPOSE WHAT THE PRESIDENT
IS DOINGI'M D.C. RESIDENT AND
WE KNOW THAT LAST TIME
PRESIDENT TRUMP WANTED TO HAVE
A MILITARY PARADE D.C.
RESIDENTS SPOKE OUT SO
FORCEFULLY AND REPRESENTATIVES
IN CITY COUNCIL SAID NO WAY.
>>  CODE PINK AGAIN WANTED TO
FLY THAT BABY TRUMP BALLOON
TWO FEET OVER THE GROUND AND
THE PARK SERVICE GROUNDED THAT
IDEA.
>>  THIS YEAR'S 4TH OF JULY
PLANS ON NATIONAL MALL FORCE
AIRPORTS TO CLOSE DOWN
TEMPORARILY.
FLIGHTS WILL BE US IS SPENDS
6:15207:HA PEOPLE FOR MILITARY
FLY OVERS AND AGAIN FROM -- OF
COURSE YOU'REEN KUNLING TO
CHECK WITH AIR LINES AND SEE
WHETHER OR NOT YOUR FLIGHT MAY
BE AFFECTED BY THIS TSA SAYS
BETWEEN TODAY AND SURPRISED
TWELVE MILLION PEOPLE WILL FLY
FOR HOLIDAY.
>>  VIRGINIA DEPARTMENT OF
TRANSPORTATION IS SECONDS
DRIVER AS I SERIOUS MESSAGE ON
THIS HOLIDAY INN A FUN WAY
THOUGH.
THE SURPRISE WAS SPOTTED ON I
59 TODAY THIS SIGN YOU'RE NOT
A NAIR WORK DON'T DRIVE LIT N
A NUTSHELL WARNING YOU NOT TO
GET BEHIND THE WHEEL IF YOU'RE
UNDER INFLUENCE.
>>> REHEARSALS ARE WRAPPING UP
FOR THE 39 APP YOU'LL CAPITOL
4th CELEBRATION HOSTED BY JOHN
STAMOS.
THEY GET TO SEE PERFORM
ANSWERS BY SESAME STREET.
OJs AND MANY OTHERS TOMORROW
WEST LAWN OF CAPITOL BUILDING.
>>  AND FEDEX FIELDS LEMING
DAWRY BAND DELAYED THE
TOYRLIER THIS YEAR WHILE MICK
JAGGER RECOVERED FROM HEART
SURGERY.
>>  ALL RIGHT THERE WAS
EARLIER FIREWORKS SHOW UP THE
ROAD AT SIX FLAGS IN LARGO.
PART OF THEME WASHING JULY 4
FEST IF YOU MISSED TONIGHT
SHOW DON'T WORRY YOU HAVE A
CHANCE OWE SEE IT SEVERAL
TIMES THIS WEEK.
FACT THE NEXT THREE NIGHTS AT
SIX FLAGS TONIGHT OR TOMORROW
NIGHT DISPLAY BEGINS AT 9:15.
>> THERE WILL ALSO BE HOLIDAY
CELEBRATIONS ALL OVER THE
REGION AND "FOX5" HAS YOU
COVERED.
FIND THE LOCAL EVENT IN YOUR
NEIGHBORHOOD AND IT'S ALL ON
THE "FOX5" APP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
MARYLAND MOTHER IS WARPING
OTHER PARENTS AFTER SHE SAID
HER SON CONTRACT AID FL
FLESH-EATING BACTERIA IN OCEAN
CITY MARYLAND.
>>  IMAGES OF HER SON'S LEGS
AND ARMS ARE DIFFICULT TO LOOK
AT.
LINDSEY WATTS IS HERE WITH THE
STORE JIXT THIS THIS IS NOT
THE ONLY CASE ON THE OOERN
SEABOARD.
>>  THERE'S BEEN SEVERAL HE OF
THESE LATELY IN CASE OF
FLORIDA WOMAN IT WAS DEADLY.
FORTUNATELY THE BOY IN OCEAN
CITY IS RECOVERING.
AND DESPITE THE PAINFUL
LOOKING INJURIES.
THIS BACTERIA IS RARE BUT
SOMETHING TO BE A WARE OF WHEN
SWIMMING.
WE WANT TO WARN YOU SOME
GRAPHICS HERE ARE HARD TO
WATCH.
>> THESE IMAGES HAVE BEEN
SHARED THOUSANDS OF TIME ON
SOCIAL MEDIA ALONG WITH
MOTHER'S MESSAGE HER SON WAS
IN WEST OCEAN CITY IMSWING IN
THE BAY NEAR ROUTE 50 A DAY
LATER NOTICED SPOTS ON HIS
BODY AND NEXT DAY THEY WERE
OPEN WOUND AND THEN DOCTORS
INFORMED STEVE HERSHORN SON
CONTRACTED VIBRIO A LEARN FROM
EATING BACK TIER YAVRMENT
LATEST UPDATE IS GOOD NEWS.
HER SON IS HEALING AND WHAT
HAPPENED COMES JUST DAYS AFTER
FLORIDA WOMAN DIED IN TAMPA
AND IT ALL STARTED WHEN T
THE-YEAR-OLD SCRAPED HER LEG
IN WATER.
>>  I TOLD MY MOM MULTIPLE
TIMES I WANT TO BE NORMAL
AGAIN.
>>  ELSEWHERE IN FLORIDA KILEY
PARK HER TO HAVE A CHUNK LEG
REMOVED AFTER WENT IN THE
OCEAN WITH SKATEBOARD INJURY
ON HER FOOT.
>>  SCUFF ON HER TOE.
I MEAN IT ALL MOST COST STEVE
HERSHORN LIFE.
>>  IT'S HARD SEEING FRIEND
AND FAMILY AND YOU KNOW ON THE
BEACH HAVING FUN BECAUSE WE
WERE THERE DOING THE SAME
THING.
>> IT ENTERS THE BODY THROUGH
KURKTS BURNS, INSECT BITES AND
IT IS RARE AND CDC SAYS MOST
THAT CONTRACT IT HAVE OTHER
HEALTH PROBLEMS M EARLY
SYMPTOMS INCLUDE WET OR SWONL
SKIN, PAIN AND FEVER.
DOCTORS SAY IT'S CRUCIAL TO
GET TREATMENT IMMEDIATELY.
>>  SMALL WOUND AND THING THAT
TER PHASE US YOU AS A DOCTOR
YOU SEE IT GET WORST RIGHT IN
FRONT EVER SDMRU NECRATIZING
FACIAITIS IS THE MEDICAL TERM
FOR THIS CONDITION.
CDC SAYS AS MANY AS ONE IN
THREE PEOPLE WITH INFECTION
END UP DYING FROM.
IT SARAH.
>>> FIREWORKS ON WALL STREET
AHEAD OF FOURTH.
LITERALLY THE DOW, THAT'S BACK
AND S&P CLOSING AT RECORD E
EYES.
TRAIINGD DAY ENDED WITH
SPARKLERS.
CELEBRATING MACY'S 4th OF JULY
FIREWORKS SPECTACULAR.
MARKETS WILL BE CLOSED
TOMORROW FOR THE HOLIDAY.
>> WELL, IF YOU HAD A LITTLE
TROUBLE POSTING TO SOCIAL
MEDIA TODAY YOU WERE NOT AL
ALONE.
WE'LL TELL WHAT YOU CAUSED
WORLDWIDE PROBLEMS AND CAUGHT
ON CAMERA A MAN ACCUSED OF
THOUGHING A LITTLE FIRE
CRACKER AT LOCAL POLICE
OFFICER SITEING IN CIRS.
AND BLUE CRAB POPULATION ON
RISE IN CHESAPEAKE BAY WHAT IT
MEANS FOR PLATE AND WALLET.
>>  COMING UP ON FINAL FIVE
THE ISSUE OF ADDING A CIT
CITIZENSHIP WE TO THE CENSUS
SAYS IT WAS SETSLED AND IT
MECHANICS OF IDEA MRTION ARE
CONFUSED OF WHAT IS GOING ON.
♪ ♪
This is how Driving Should Feel.
The Tech-advanced Nissan LEAF.
The Best Selling Electric
Vehicle of All Time.
This is Nissan
Intelligent Mobility.
♪
.  HERE'S A LOOK AT TOP
STORIES WE'RE FOLLOWING
TONIGHT ANOTHER LEGAL SETBACK
FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP EFFORTS TO
BUILD A BORDER LAWCH THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT CANNOT INTO
DEFENSE MONEY TO BUILD IN
SECTIONS OF WALL ARIZONA AND
NEW MEXICO AND THE RULING
UPHELD A LOWER COURT.
TUPZ CLEAR IF THEY'LL APPEAL.
>>  PRINCE GEORGE COUNTY
POLICE OFFICER A MAN AKUSDZ OF
THROWING LIT FIRE CRACKER
INSIDE A CRUISER.
INVESTIGATORS DETERMINE THE
INCIDENT WAS PREPLANNED
BECAUSE SOMEONE REPORT TODAY
ON THEIR PHONE.
FORTUNATELY THE OFFICER WAS
NOT HURT.
POLICE HAVE IDENTIFIED A
PERSON OF INTEREST.
>> THE DRIVER OF A CAR DIED ON
THE SCENE AFTER A CRASH WITH A
TRUCK IN MONTGOMERY COUNTRY.
IT HAPPENED AROUND 3 P.M. IN
POOLS VILING RIVER ROAD AND
OLD RIVER ROADS AND CRASH
CAUSED A UTILITY POLE TO SNAP
AND HALF AND TOOK DOWN POWER
LINES.
NO WORD WHAT CAUSED THAT CR
CRASH.
>>  FUNERAL SERVICES WERE HELD
TODAY FOR RETIRED NYPD
DETECTIVE FOUGHT TO MAKE SURE
9/11 RESPONDS VERZ NEVER
FORGOTTEN.
HE HAD COLORECTAL CANCER AND
HE ATTRIBUTED TO DIGGING
THROUGH RUBBLE.
TODAY HE WAS REMEMBERED AS
BRAVE AND FAITHFUL MAN.
>>  AT THE END OF THE DAY
THROUGHOUT HIS REMARKABLE LIFE
HE WANTED TO DO WHAT WAS
RIGHTS AND DESPERATELY WANTED
AREAS PARTICULARLY THOSE IN
POSITIONS OF GREAT POWER TO
FOLLOW SUIT.
>>  JUNE ALVAREZ AND JOHN
STEWART GOT EMOTIONAL WHEN
THEY TESTIFIED BEFORE CONGRESS
HOPING TO CONVINCE LAW MAKERS
TO PASSE BILL TO CONTINUE
FUNDING THE 9/11 VICTIM
COMPENSATION FUND.
>>  EYE VICTIM WAS ELDERLY
WOMAN IN ANNE ARRUNDEL.
TIPS TO STAY COOL.
DRINK LOTS OF FLUIDS AND AVOID
DIRECT SURPRISE LIGHT AND TAKE
IT EASY WITH OUTDOOR ACTIVITY.
JUST A REMINDER FOR YOU.
>>  CRAB LOVERS A NEW REPORT
REVEALS CHESAPEAKE BLUE CRAB
POPULATION SURPRISE AND PEOPLE
THAT RUN THE CRAB HAS SAID
GROWING POPULATION WILL NOT
MOST LIKELY TRANSLATE TO LOWER
PRICES.
>>  POPULATION INCREASE IS NOT
THAT MUCH OF POPULATION
INCREASE WHEN IT COMES TO
PRICE BECOMING LESS.
THERE'S MORE OF THEM BUT NOT
MORE OF A LOT, MORE A LITTLE.
>>  NOW FROM BAY TO STOREY OF
UNDER THE SEA.
SUE SOME.
>>  YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
>>  NO, NO, BAILEY.
>> SHE'S A SINGER.
>> WHAT A BEAUTIFUL WEDNESDAY.
TIME LAPSE VIDEO FROM FR
FRIENDSHIP HEIGHTS
NEIGHBORHOOD FROM NORTHEAST
D.C.
>>  DAN CAPLE GATE SHOPPED
THIS THERE SAY CHANCE WE WILL
NOT HAVE THAT PICTURESQUE
SCENE TOMORROW.
>>  I'M HOPING WE CAN CLEAR
OUT BY FIRE WORKS.
SHOWERS AND THUNDERSTORMS AND
DODGE AGO AROUND THAT TOMORROW
AND PEAK TIME PROBABLY 1206
SGLERLIER MEANS LET'S TRY TO
GET IT WRAPPED UP AT LEAST IN
MOOIPD MY MIND.
>>  RED, WHITE AND BLUE FOR
YOU.
>>  LOOK AT THAT CAPITAL WH
WHEEL.
>>  LIT UP TONIGHT.
>>  THAT WHEEL PUTS ON A SHOW
NIGHT AFTER NIGHT.
>> AND WE LOVER TO DISPLAY IT
FOUR.
BEAUTIFUL EVENING OUT.
THERE WARM, CLEAR.
AND STORMS STAYED AWAY FROM
METRO TODAY.
IN FACT WE BARELY GOT ANYTHING
ANYWHERE CLOSE BY.
IT WAS NICE TO HAVE A NIGHT
OFF FROM THAT.
DESPITE HOT AND HUMID DAY.
ALL RED, WHITE AND BLUE AS WE
GO TO TOMORROW.
CAN'T LET WEATHER STOP YOU AND
BE INSIDE MAYBE IF YOU KNOW
YOU'RE OUT BY POOL OUT DOING
BARBEQUEING AAND SKIES DARKEN
AND RAIN COMES DOWN.
LIQUID SAID TODAY GEORGOUS 4TH
OF JULY EAVE.
HOPEFULLY CERTAIN IN FULL FEST
ACTIVITY MODE.
BEAUTIFUL SUNSET CAPTURED BY
WILL ON TWITTER IN OLNEY AS
YOU SEE LAST OF SUN FLIPPING
BELOW THE HOR EYE ZONE AND IN
FACT IT WAS I HOT SUMMER DAY.
93 WAS MAGIC NUMBER FOR REG
APP, DULLES, BWI.
IT WAS HOT OUT THERE AND ABOVE
NORMAL.
IT WAS ALSO HUMID.
AND THOSE HEAT UP DEVELOP
VALUES WERE GETTING CLOSE TO
AND IN SOME PLACES PASSING
EARLIER THIS AFTERNOON.
3 IN THE DISTRICT.
WIND OUT OF THE NORTH WEST.
THAT SAVED US TODAY THAT
PREVENTED STORMS FROM
INITIATING.
WE WERE QUIET INTO THE
OVERNIGHT.
83 OUT IN THE DISTRICT.
WARM, 4 ANNAPOLIS.
WE FAENL BACK UP TOER 70S.
NORTH AND 77 FREDERICK AND
REALLY DEPOSIT GET ANYTHING
LOCAL.
TOMORROW DIFFERENT STORY BIT
OF SYSTEM COMING THROUGH.
SO THAT REALLY TAPS INTO HEAT
AND HUMIDITY AND INITIATES
STORMS.
00 NOTHING.
QUIING CHANGE TO NOON HOUR.
GETTING STARTED EARLY ON THE
STORMS WE EXPECT SHOWERS AND
THUNDERSTORMS.
THAT'S A LOT OF COVERAGE.
EVERYONE SEIZE RAIN AT SOME
POINT.
AREAS WEST LOOK FAVORED.
HERE'S 5:00 ACROSS I 11 IS
DOWN TO I 64 CORRIDOR.
TALKING ABOUT HEAVY RAIN
POTENTIAL THERE.
9:00 MOST IS DPAID AWAY.
YOU MAY HAVE WET GROUNDS OUT.
THERE SEVERE THREAT IS NOT TOO
HIGH.
MAYBE DAMAGING WIND HERE OR
THERE.  WE HAVE TO KEEP AN EYE
ON HEAVY RAIN THREAT AND
POTENTIAL FOR FLOODING IF WE
GETET STORMS ONE AFTER THE
OTHER TOMORROW.
>>  92 FOR HIGH SCATTERED
TEMPERATURES AND STORMS ON THE
FOURTH SORE DIDN'T JUST THE
WAY IT IS THIS YEAR AND THE
WAY IT STAYS FOR THE HOLIDAY
WEEKEND.
PRESIDENT TRUMP PUT FWUD U.S.
SOCCER TEAM ON HOLD SORT.
IT WILL SEND MEMBERS TO FRANCE
FOR FINAL GAME SUNDAY.
OF COURSE BE U.S. FACING OFF
AGAINST NETHERLANDS.
LAST WEEK PRESIDENT RANTSED ON
TWITTER ABOUT MID FIELDER
MEGAN RAMPINO.
MONTHS AGO SHE SAID SHE WOULD
NOT GO TO THE WHITE HOUSE IF
THE TEAM WON AND REFUSED TO
SING NATIONAL ANTHEM DURING
WORLD IT UP TO SHOW OPPOSITION
TO TRUMP ADMINISTRATION.
>>  15 CONTESTANTS WINNER
MOLLY SCHUYLER 8:32 AND WALKED
WAY WITH 1500 PRIZE.
THIS IS THE TIME THEY HEL THAT
EVENT.
>>  DAVID BRUDNELLY ONE OF TOP
COMPETITIVE HEAT NERTZ WORLD
SCARFING THEM DOWN.
HE DOMINATED HERE TONIGHT.
THEY GAVE IT THEIR ALL.
BIG SHOUT-OUT TO JUS TIRNGS
LYNN CIRCUMSTANCE BRANDON AN
COOP.
THEY GAVE IT THEIR BEST.
>>  LINDSAY WAS DAINTY CHEWING
AND COVERING HER MOUTH
SOMETHING WOW NOT SEE IN
BURGER EAST CHAMPIONSHIP.
>>  EVERYBODY ELSE WAS
CHUGGING IT DOWN.
>>  SHE GOT A FOUVRJ BURGER
IN.
JUSTIN GOT ALMOST ALL OF.
IT.
>>  I DON'T KNOW HOW THEY DO.
IT WE CALLED HER SILENT ASAS
SGLIN CHEERING HER ON.
>>  YES YOU.
>> GOT THIS GIRL LET'S GO
RECEIPTS GO LET'S GO.
>>  IS THAT WHAT YOU WERE
SGLAIING EAT MORE EAT MOORE.
>>  LIKE A DRILL SERGEANT
SHAWN MY GOSH POOR LINDSAY
COACH.
>> I WAS ROOTING FOR HER I
WANTED HER TO WIN.
>> THANKS FOR DOING THAT.
>>  ALL RIGHT.
AND COMING UP, SEEMS LIKE NO
BRAINIER AND PEOPLE SHOULD
KNOW TO PRACTICE SAFETY BEHIND
THE WHEEL.
WE'LL SHOW YOU VIDEO OF A
CRASH THAT LAND AID SUSPECTED
DRUNK DRIVER IN HANDCUFFS AND
BEHIND BARS.
THAT'S NEXT.
This is not a bed.
It's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed is on sale now
during our Lowest
Prices of the Season.
It senses your movement,
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
It even helps with this.
So you wake up ready to
hit the ground running.
Don't miss our 4th of
July Special with the
queen Sleep Number 360
c4 smart bed now $1299.
Plus, free premium delivery
when you add a base.
Ends Sunday.
Sleep Number.
Proven, quality sleep.
>> REMINDER NOT TO DRINK AND
DRIVE.
A POLICE OFFICER WAS DRIVING
DOWN THE ROAD AND I VEHICLE
APPEARED GOING THE WRONG WAY.
THE DRIVER OF THAT VEHICLE WAS
UNDER THE INFLUENCE THE
OFFICER TURNED ON EMERGENCY
LIGHTS BUT THAT DID NOT STOP
THE DRIVER FROM LAMB SLAMMING
INTO THE OFFICER'S PATROL CAR.
THANKFULLY NO ONE WAS INJURED
AND THE DRIVER WAS ARRESTED
AND FACES SEVERAL CHARGES.
>>  BE CAREFUL WITH CELL HOPE
TO AS YOU CELEBRATE THIS
HOLIDAY.
TECH COMPANY ASSUREIAN SAYS
IT'S MOST DANGEROUS TIME FOR
PHONE.
CRACKED SCREAMS INCREASED BY
40%.
WORST CULPRIT WATER DAMAGE
THAT GOES UP NEARLY 250%
DURING HOLIDAY WEEKEND.
KEEP THEM AWAY FROM THE POOL.
>>  IF YOU HAVE BEEN HAVING
TROUBLE WITH SOCIAL MEDIA
ACCOUNT YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
U.S. ERS.
>> Reporter:ED BUGS SUCH AS
INCHAGE S NOT LOADING.
NO OW DID WE LIVE TWOUT.
>>  WE HAD TO TALK TO SBHB IT.
>>  UP NEXT, ONE FUNERAL TO
CHECK OF HOLIDAY FORECAST.
>>  WE'LL BE BE RIGHT BACK.
♪ ♪
This is how Driving Should Feel.
The Tech-advanced Nissan LEAF.
The Best Selling Electric
Vehicle of All Time.
This is Nissan
Intelligent Mobility.
♪
Come see what's NEW this summer
at Busch Gardens
and Water Country USA.
Soar 80 feet high on the new
Finnegan's Flyer.
Then blast off on the new
Cutback Water Coaster.
And experience a whole different
park after dark
at Busch Gardens Summer Nights.
Enjoy your favorite thrills into
the night,
with new entertainment each week
featuring stars from America's
Got Talent.
Right now, save up to 50% on
tickets.
Busch Gardens and Water Country
USA.
>> GI GROOM FIRST LOOK AT
BRIDE BEFORE WEDDING TOUCHED
OUT TO BE A BIG PRANK.
TAKE A LOOK [ LAUGHTER ].
>> SO THE GROOM ACTUALLY
TURNED TO SEE HIS VEILED BRIDE
WAS HIS LITTLE BROTHER WHOSE A
U.S. ARMY SERGEANT TOOK NREV
MOST GERM NO, I FULFILL DUTIES
AS BEST MAN AND HE WAS
STANDING THERE IN HIS MOTHER'S
WEDDING GOWN.
>>  THAT'S REALLY SGLUT IT
WAS.
>>  WHAT A COMPANY.
>> I LOVE HOW HE COULD NOT FIT
INTO THE WEDDING GOWN EITHER
BY THE WAY.
>>  NICE OF MOM TO LET HIM PUT
IT ON I WOULD BE LIKE NO DUDE
YOU'RE NOT WEARING MY WEDDING
DRESS.
>>  NOT MY SON.
>>  JIM LOKAY IS UP NEXT WITH
THE FINAL FIVE.
>>  HAVE A GREAT NIGHT.