[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
FREMANTLE MEDIA]
[CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--]
WOMAN: ♪ MADE IN GEORGIA ♪
.
>>> RIGHT NOW AT 8:00.
WINTER WEATHER, FROM SNOW, TO
THE ICE TO THE RAIN.
WE CAN SEE IT ALL.
WHEN WILL THE FLAKES START TO
FALL? .
>>> PLUS, BEWARE OF COUNTERFEIT
CASH.
FAKE BILLS MAKING THEIR WAY
AROUND NORTHERN VIRGINIA.
HOW YOU CAN SPOT THE PHONY
MOTHER.
>> RUNNING OUT OF OPTIONS,
JUSSIE SMOLLETT'S LAWYER ADAMANT
THE EMPIRE STAR WAS NOT INVOLVED
IN AN ALLEGED ATTACK.
BUT TONIGHT, QUESTIONS ARE
MOUNTING.
>>> YOUR NEWS STARTS NOW.
>>> OFF THE TOP AT 8, DC REGION
IS IN FOR A BLAST OF WINTER
WEATHER.
A WINTER STORM WARNING IS SET TO
TAKE EFFECT OVERNIGHT.
BY THE END OF IT ALL, COULD SEE
A MESS OF SNOW, SLEET AND RAIN.
TOMORROW IS ALREADY A SNOW DAY
FOR A NUMBER OF SCHOOLS IN OUR
AREA THAT HAS A LOT OF CHILDREN
PROBABLY SAYING YAY.
WE HAVE A FULL LIST SCROLLING AT
THE BOTTOM OF YOUR SCREEN.
>> RIGHT TO CAITLIN ROTH WITH
THE LATEST ON THE STORM.
HEY CAITLIN.
>> HEY THERE.
AT LEAST THE KIDS ARE HAPPY.
YES, A SNOW DAY FOR SO MANY,
GUYS.
IT WILL BE VERY PROBLEMATIC IF
YOU DO HAVE TO GO TO WORK
TOMORROW.
SO MANY OF US DO.
WINTER STORM IMPACTING BOTH
COMMUTES.
PROBABLY MORE SIGNIFICANT IN THE
MORNING WHEN FULL ON SNOW FOR
JUST ABOUT EVERYONE
TRANSITIONING TO ICY MIX IN THE
AFTERNOON.
HERE IN THE METRO TALKING ABOUT
JUST RAIN BY THE EVENING
COMMUTE.
WON'T BE THE CASE NORTH AND
WEST.
WINTER STORM WARNINGS IN PINK.
HIGH IMPACT EVENT.
A LITTLE LESS IMPACTFUL SOUTH
AND EAST, PURPLE AREA, WINTER
WEATHER ADVISORY, NORTHERN NECK
OF VIRGINIA.
EXTREME SOUTHERN MARYLAND OVER
TO THE EASTERN SHORE.
HERE'S OUR STORM RIGHT NOW.
IT LOOKS HUGE.
IT IS SPRAWLING FROM THE
CAROLINA COAST LINE TO NEBRASKA
SNOW AND RAIN AND EVERYTHING IN
BETWEEN.
BIG CLASSIC GULF COAST STORM.
BRINGING IN ALL THAT MOISTURE AS
IT HEADS IN OUR DIRECTION.
HOURS AWAY, SEE THE BEGINNING,
PRECIPITATION ONLY IN SOUTHWEST
VIRGINIA.
A NUMBER OF HOURS TO GO.
BUT THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE
FOR SNOW ARRIVAL TIMES.
CENTRAL VIRGINIA, AFTER MIDNIGHT
TO ABOUT 2 A.M.
YOU GET TO OUR FAR-REACHING
WESTERN SUBURBS, SHAR SLOTSVILLE
UP THROUGH CULPEPER, WINCHESTER
81 ABOUT 2 TO 4:00 A.M.
4 TO 6 METRO.
NORTH AND EAST OF PRINCE
GEORGE'S COUNTY BALTIMORE, UP 95
TOWARDS PENNSYLVANIA YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT AFTER 6 A.M.
SO MOST OF US WILL BE WAKING UP
IT'S SNOWING IT WILL BE SNOWING
ON AND OFF HEAVY AT TIMES
THROUGH THE MORNING AND THAT
WILL ALLOW THOSE ACCUMULATIONS
TO PILE UP THROUGH THE EARLY
AFTERNOON.
WE'RE THINKING A SOLID THREE TO
FIVE ALONG 59 INCLUDING
WASHINGTON.
FIVE TO EIGHT, JACKPOT AREA
NORTH AND WEST.
A LITTLE LESS THAN ADVISORY AREA
ONE TO THREE DOWN IN
SOUTHEASTERN PARTS OF OUR
VIEWING AREA.
ICING ALSO A BIG CONCERN.
ONCE WE TRANSITION TO FREEZING
RAIN AND SLEET, WE COULD HAVE
SIGNIFICANT ICING POSSIBLE WHERE
IT HOLDS ON LONGER ALONG THE 81
CORRIDOR FAR NORTHWEST UP INTO
THE MOUNTAINS.
A LOT TO TALK ABOUT WITH
CHALLENGING WINTER STORM
TOMORROW.
I WILL GO THROUGH THE HOUR BY
HOUR FORECAST WITH YOU, AS WELL
AS SOME NICER DAYS AHEAD IN THE
SEVEN-DAY.
STILL COMING UP, GUY.
>>  MEANWHILE CREWS IN MARYLAND
PRETREATING ROADS AHEAD OF THE
STORM.
SKY FOX OVER COLLEGE PARK THIS
MORNING AS CREWS PUT DOWN BRINE
ON THE MAJOR HIGHWAYS.
THEY WANT DRIVERS TO REMEMBER TO
GIVE EXTRA SPACE AS THEY PREP
THE ROADS.
>>  THE MAIN MESSAGE FOR FOLK TO
STAY HOME.
THE FEWER VEHICLES THAT ARE OUT
TOMORROW, ESPECIALLY WHEN
PRECIPITATION IS COMING DOWN,
FIRST THE SNOW AND ICE AND
SLEET, IT WILL BE GRATUITOUS FOR
OUR TRUCKS IN TERMS OF LESS
TRAFFIC OUT THERE.
FOR FOLKS THAT DO VENTURE OUT, I
DON'T KNOW WHY THEY WOULD DO
THAT, WE WANT THEM TO OBVIOUSLY
FALL BEHIND OUR SNOW PLOWS.
>>  JUST A REMINDER IF YOU
HAVEN'T ALREADY DONE SO, NOW
WOULD BE A VERY GOOD TIME TO
DOWNLOAD "FOX5" WEATHER APP FOR
UP TO THE MINUTE FOLKS WHEN THE
STORM STARTS AND END, EVERYTHING
IN BETWEEN.
"FOX5" WEATHER APP DOWNLOAD IT
NOW.
>> TONIGHT THREE PEOPLE ARE HURT
AFTER A TRIPLE SHOOTING IN
WASHINGTON DC.
ONE OF THEM IS IN CRITICAL
CONDITION.
THIS ALL HAPPEN AROUND 1 O'CLOCK
THIS AFTERNOON ON ELI PLACE
SOUTHEAST DC, NEAR THE FORD
DUPONT PARK.
FOUR ADULT ONES ONE JUVENILE CAR
ALL BULLET WOUNDS.
SPEAKING TO PEOPLE IN THE
NEIGHBORHOODS, SEVERAL SAY
INCIDENTS LIKE THIS ARE RARE.
>> USUALLY THERE'S NOT A LOT OF
COPS ON THIS STREET
PARTICULARLY.
IT HASN'T BEEN -- IT'S NOT A
ROUGH NEIGHBORHOOD.
AT LOT OF KID THAT IS LIVE
AROUND HERE, MY KIDS COME AROUND
HERE.
SO IT'S JUST IF -- IT'S JUST
LIKE CRAZY THAT THIS EVEN
HAPPEN.
>> POLICE STILL INVESTIGATING
AND SEARCHING FOR A GRAY HYUNDAI
THAT MAY HAVE BEEN INVOLVED IN
THAT SHOOTING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SOME GOOD NEWS FOR THE HOCKEY
ARENA IN SOUTHEAST DC, FRIEND
IT'S OF FORT DUPONT ARENA
REACHED A DEAL.
TWO RINKS FOR NEW ARENA, COAST
OF A NEW HOME IS 21 MILLION
DOLLARS.
DEAL WOULD REQUIRE THE GROUP TO
RAISE 3 MILLION DOLLARS OVER THE
NEXT YEAR TO HELP WITH THE COST
OF CONSTRUCTION.
IF YOU WANT TO HELP WITH EFFORT,
GROUP STARTED GOFUNDME PAGE.
FIND SOME OF THAT INFORMATION ON
OUR WEBSITE FOX5DC.COM.
>> NEW DETAILS ON A STORY THAT
"FOX5" HAS BEEN FOLLOWING.
A MANASSAS YOUTH PASTOR BLEED
GUILTY IN CHILD SEX ABUSE CASE
SET TO BEGIN NEXT WEEK.
JORDAN BAIRD FACED TWO COUNTS OF
INDECENT LIBERTY.
TEEN FROM THE LIGHT CHURCH 16 AT
THE TIME SAID BAIRD KISSED HER
EXPOSED HIMSELF AND ASKED HER TO
PERFORM ORAL SEX.
THE YOUNG WOMAN'S FAMILY ALSO
SUING THE LIFE CHURCH FOR 21
MILLION DOLLARS.
BAIRD WAS CONVICTED LAST YEAR OF
SEXUALLY ABUSING ANOTHER
16-YEAR-OLD FROM THAT CHURCH.
>> GUNMAN WHO OPENED FIRE AT
ARUNDEL MILLS MALL IN HANOVER
MARYLAND OVER THE WEEKEND NOW IN
POLICE CUSTODY, WE SHOULD SAY
ALLEGED GUNMAN.
POLICE SAY TWO GROUPS GOT INTO
ARGUMENT.
16-YEAR-OLD JAMARI HAMMOND
ALLEGEDLY STARTED SHOOTING.
ONE MAN SHOT AND TAKEN TO THE
HOSPITAL.
IS EXPECTED TO RECOVER.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP'S NATIONAL
EMERGENCY DECLARATION IS FACING
SEVERAL LEGAL CHALLENGES.
VIRGINIA AND MARYLAND HAVE
JOINED MORE THAN 12 OTHER STATES
THAT HAVE FILED SUIT AGAINST THE
PRESIDENT'S PLAN TO SHIFT
FEDERAL THERES TO BUILD A WALL
ALONG U.S. AND MEXICO BORDER.
EARLIER TODAY SPOKE WITH
MARYLAND ATTORNEY GENERAL BRINE
FROSH SAID THE PRESIDENT'S
ACTION VIOLATES THE CONSTITUTION
BY STEPPING ON POURS OF CONGRESS
AND EXECUTIVE BRANCH.
>> WHAT DONALD TRUMP IS
PROPOSING HE BE IMPERIL
PRESIDENT.
HE HAVE UNLIMITED EXECUTIVE
POURS.
CONGRESS HAVE MADE IT VERY
CLEAR, THEY ARE NOT GIVING HIM
MONEY TO BUILD A WALL.
HE'S SAYING NEVER MIND I'M JUST
GOING TO BUILD IT ANYHOW.
THAT'S UNCONSTITUTIONAL.
>> VIRGINIA STATE'S ATTORNEY
MARK HERRING ALSO SLAMMED THE
PRESIDENT'S DECLARATION, HERRING
CALLED IT A FAKE EMERGENCY.
>>> ADD A FAMILIAR NAME TO
DEMOCRATIC FIELD FOR VIRGINIA.
VERMONT SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS
MAKING ANOTHER RUN FOR THE WHITE
HOUSE.
HE LOST THE DEMOCRATIC
NOMINATION TO HILLARY CLINTON
BACK IN 2016.
EXPECTED TO FOCUS HIS CAMPAIGN
ON UNIVERSAL HEALTHCARE, FREE
COLLEGE AND CLIMATE CHANGE.
OF COURSE FACING A CROWDED
FIELD, CORY BOOKER, KAMALA
HARRIS AND ELIZABETH WARREN JUST
TO NAME A FEW.
>> NEW TONIGHT IN THE CASE OF A
MAN SETTING A FIRE IN PIZZERIA
RESTAURANT IN NORTHWEST DC.
AFTER HEARING ALL THE EVIDENCE
IN THE CASE, JUDGE ORDERED THE
ARSON SUSPECT HELD WITHOUT BOND
UNTIL TRIAL.
IN COURT TODAY IT WAS ALSO
REVEALED THAT THE SUSPECT HAS
BEEN ARRESTED TWICE NOW AT THE
WASHINGTON MONUMENT.
PAUL WAGNER PICKS UP THE STORY
FROM THERE.
>> PROSECUTORS SAY HE WAS
FIGHTING WITH TWO U.S. PARK
POLICE OFFICERS BACK IN
FEBRUARY.
HIS NAME IS RYAN RAMOS.
BACK ON FEBRUARY 4TH HE JUMPED A
FENCE AT WASHINGTON MONUMENT AND
REFUSED TO COOPERATE WITH THE
OFFICERS WHO WERE TRYING TAKE
HIM INTO CUSTODY.
INSTEAD HE FOUGHT BACK, HITTING
ONE OFFICER IN THE FACE CAUSING
A BLOODY NOSE FOR OFFICERS
USED'S.BATON IN ATTEMPT TO GET
HIM ON THE GROUND BEFORE FINALLY
USING A TASER.
AFTER GOING BEFORE A JUDGE WHO
TOLD HIM TO STAY AWAY FROM THE
MONUMENT, HE WENT BACK THE VERY
NEXT DAY.
U.S. PARK POLICE FOUND HIM
INSIDE THE MONUMENT THIS TIME
AND WHEN HE WAS TAKEN INTO
CUSTODY, HE TOLD THE POLICE A
THIRD TIME IS A CHARGE.
BUT IT WAS HIS ALLEGED BEHAVIOR
AT PING PONG BACK ON JANUARY
23RD THAT SEEMED TO BOTHER THE
JUDGE THE MOST.
PROSECUTORS SHOWED FIRST THE
DEFENSE AND THEN THE JUDGE, A
TWO MINUTE VIDEO, APPARENTLY
RECORDED INSIDE THE RESTAURANT.
WE WERE NOT PERMITTED TO SEE IT.
BUT PROSECUTORS TOLD THE JUDGE
ACCELERANT WAS FOUND AT THE
SCENE, THE FLAMES SHOT UP THE
SIDE OF THE ROOM VERY QUICKLY
AND WHEN HE LEFT THE RESTAURANT,
HE PUNCHED A SURVEILLANCE
CAMERA.
IT IS STILL UNCLEAR WHY THE MAN
CAME HERE TO WASHINGTON AND WHAT
HIS ULTIMATE MOTIVE MAY HAVE
BEEN.
THE PROSECUTOR IN THE CASE SAID
THAT THIS MAN WAS APPARENTLY
LIVING OUT OF HIS CAR FOR THE
LAST TWO WEEKS.
NOW, AS YOU MAY RECALL A LITTLE
BIT MORE THAN TWO YEARS AGO, MAN
WENT TO THAT SAME RESTAURANT
WITH AR-15 AND SHOT UP THE
INSIDE OF THE RESTAURANT,
BELIEVING THAT THERE WERE YOUNG
CHILDREN BEING HELD THERE
AGAINST THEIR WILL.
ONE OTHER NOTE, THE PARENTS OF
HIM WAS HERE TODAY.
THEY WERE SITTING IN THE GALLERY
AND THEY HAD WITH THEM A STUFFED
ANIMAL.
A CURIOUS GEORGE, THAT THEY
PROPPED UP ON SOME BOOKS AND
POINTED TOWARDS THEIR SON,
SEEMINGLY SO HE COULD SEE IT.
>>  BACK TO YOU IN THE STUDIO.
>> STILL TO COME, ANOTHER TWIST
IN THE JUSSIE SMOLLETT
INVESTIGATION.
THE FBI NOW GETTING INVOLVED.
NOW IT LOOKS LIKE THE CASE COULD
COST HIM SOME SCREEN TIME.
>> PLUS WARNING TONIGHT.
FAKE CASH MAKES ITS WAY AROUND
NORTHERN VIRGINIA.
HOW YOU CAN SPOT THE REAL DEAL
FROM THE COUNTERFEIT.
>>> ♪ ♪
.
>>> DEVELOPING TONIGHT WAS A
HATE CRIME OR WAS IT A HOAX.
JUSSIE SMOLLETT'S LAWYERS INSIST
THE EMPIRE ACTOR DID NOT
ORCHESTRATE HIS OWN ASSAULT
DESPITE WIDESPREAD SPECULATION
HE PAID TWO MEN TO ATTACK HIM ON
CHICAGO STREET.
NICK IN THE NEWSROOM WITH THE
LATEST.
>>REPORTER:  ATTORNEYS FOR
JUSSIE SMOLLETT SAID THE
36-YEAR-OLD HAS NO PLANS TO MEET
WITH THE CHICAGO POLICE ABOUT
HIS ALLEGED ATTACK.
EVEN AS THE ACTOR FACING
MOUNTING QUESTIONS ABOUT THE
VALIDITY OF HIS CLAIMS.
TWO BROTHERS WHO WERE INITIALLY
QUESTIONED AN RELEASED
REPORTEDLY TOLD POLICE SMOLLETT
PAID THEM TO REHEARSE AND CARRY
OUT THE ASSAULT.
THEY ALSO SAID SMOLLETT WAS
UPSET THERE WASN'T ENOUGH
ATTENTION BEING PAID TO A
THREATENING LETTER HE HAD
RECEIVED WEEKS BEFORE.
THE FBI HAS JOINED A SEPARATE
PROBE INTO THAT MAILING.
AND INVESTIGATORS BELIEVE
SMOLLETT MAY HAVE SENT THE
LETTER TO HIMSELF.
WE'RE ALSO LEARNING SEGMENTS OF
TV SHOW EMPIRE FEATURING
SMOLLETT HAVE BEEN DRASTICALLY
CUT.
ACCORDING TO TMZ UP GOING
EPISODES GETTING REWRITES, FOR
DRAMATIC SCENES AND MUSICAL
PERFORMS AN ON HIS CHARACTER.
>> HARVEY LEVIN SPEAKING ABOUT
HOW OTHER MEMBERS OF EMPIRE CAST
ARE HANDLING THE DEVELOPMENTS.
>> THERE'S A LOT OF DISBELIEF
AMONG THE EMPIRE CAST AND CREW.
PEOPLE WE'VE SPOKEN WITH.
IT IS HARD FOR THEM, BECAUSE
JUSSIE IS A VERY WELL LIKED GUY,
BOTH ON EMPIRE AND OUTSIDE OF
EMPIRE.
AND PEOPLE ARE HAVING A HARD
TIME PROCESSING THIS.
AGAIN, THERE'S -- YOU KNOW, IT'S
NOT CEMENTED THAT HE DID THIS,
BUT THERE IS NOW A LOT OF
EVIDENCE AND I THINK WE'VE
TALKED TO YOU GUYS ABOUT THIS
ALREADY, THAT COPS WERE
SUSPICIOUS ALMOST FROM THE
BEGINNING HERE:  IT JUST DIDN'T
ALL ADD UP.
PEOPLE ARE HAVING A HARD TIME
PROCESSING THIS.
>> EARLIER TODAY IT WAS REPORTED
THAT POLICE WERE INVESTIGATING A
TIP THAT SOMEONE SAW SMOLLETT IN
AN ELEVATOR WITH THE TWO
BROTHERS ON THE NIGHT OF THE
REPORTED ATTACK.
BUT POLICE NOW SAY THAT TIP HAS
BEEN DEEMED NOT CREDIBLE.
>>> FAKE $100 BILLS PASSED IN
STAFFORD COUNTY.
THE SHERIFF'S OFFICE SAYS THERE
ARE SOME CLEAR SIGNS SOMETHING
WRONG WITH THE BILLS.
THE FIRST THE BILLS ARE MISSING
THE PHRASE, IN GOD WE TRUST.
ANOTHER CLUE, IF YOU LOOK
CLOSELY YOU'LL SEE FOR MOTION
PICTURE USE ONLY.
THAT'S CLEARLY PRINTED ON THE
BILL.
BUT SOME PEOPLE CAN ACTUALLY
MISS THAT.
>> I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO TELL
WHICH ONE.
I'D HAVE TO LOOK A BILL I
ALREADY OWN AND THEN LOOK AT IT.
BUT, I MEAN IF YOU LOOK AT IT
FIRST GLANCE, NO.
>> THE TOP ONE ACTUALLY SAYS FOR
MOTION PICTURE USE ONLY.
>> WOW.
OK.
YEAH.
SO I WOULD HAVE TO LOOK REALLY
CLOSE AT IT THEN.
NO, IF YOU GET IT LIKE THAT
REALLY FAST, YOU CAN'T TELL.
>> TWO PEOPLE HAVE BEEN ARRESTED
FOR CIRCULATING FAKE ONE.
ONE WAS REPORTEDLY CARRYING FAKE
HUNDREDS AND FAKE $20 BILLS AS
WELL.
>> SPORTS BETTING COMING TO DC,
CITY COUNCIL APPROVED THE BILL
TO ALLOW GAMBLING ON SPORTS.
DC LOTTERY WILL OVERSEE THIS NEW
VENT TOUR.
COUNCIL VOTE 8-46789 SOME
COUNCIL MEMBERS UPSET DC LOTTERY
AWARDED CONTRACT WITHOUT
COMPETITIVE BIDDING.
DISTRICT JOINS A HANDFUL OF
OTHER STATES TO LEGALIZE SPORTS
BETTING AFTER SUPREME COURT OKED
THE PRACTICE.
SPORTS BETTING IN THE DISTRICT
LIKELY TO DEBUT THIS FALL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE ARE DEBUTING SNOW IN THE NEXT
COMES HOURS.
CLOCK IS TICKING.
>> BE HERE BY THE TIME YOU WAKE
UP.
SNOW ARRIVING BEFORE SUNRISE.
DIFFICULT MORNING COMMUTE.
ALL THE SCHOOLS CALLED OFF.
RIGHT THING TO DO.
IT'S GOING TO BE CHALLENGING ALL
DAY LONG, TOMORROW.
SNOW DAY FOR A LOT OF HAPPY KIDS
AND PROBABLY NOT HAPPY PARENTS
BECAUSE WE'VE HAD SEVERAL
ALREADY THIS WINTER.
THIS IS ONE THAT ACTUALLY REALLY
WARRANTS IT, NOT THAT THE OTHERS
HAVEN'T.
WE HAVEN'T HAD A BIG STORM
DURING THE WEEK YET.
REMEMBER OUR BIG ONE IN EARLY
JANUARY, THAT WAS ON A WEEKEND.
FOR THOSE WHO CAN'T STAY
HUNKERED DOWN, YOU'LL HAVE A FEW
OBSTACLES GETTING OUT THE DOOR
TOMORROW AND EVEN COMING HOME IN
PARTS OF0 YOU ARE AREA.
SNOW ARRIVES AREA, 3 TO 6 A.M.
5 TO 6.
>>  SO HEAVY HIGH SNOWFALL RATES
UP TO INCH AN HOUR, PRETTY
CONVECTIVE.
GOOD MOISTURE INTO THE STORM AND
YOU CAN GET THAT SNOW TO COME
DOWN REAL FAST.
SO WE ARE EXPECTED TO TRANSITION
TO A MIX AND THEN RAIN DURING
THE AFTERNOON AND EVENING.
BUT FOR AREAS FAR NORTH AND
WEST, HARD TO TRANSITION, ICE
CAN HOLD ON LONGER AND WE'LL
HAVE BIGGER ISSUES THERE.
STORM I SHOWED YOU EARLIER HUGE,
TENNESSEE VALLEY AND MIDWEST
RIGHT NOW.
BY MORNING IT WILL HAVE SNOW
THAT EXTENDS FROM CHICAGO ALL
THE WAY TO DC.
BUT IT'S STILL PRETTY FAR SOUTH
OF US, WE DON'T EXPECT ANYTHING
FOR THE NEXT FEW HOURS.
39 IN WASHINGTON RIGHT NOW.
COLD, CHILLY ALL DAY, ALREADY
SEEING SOME PLACES AT FREEZING,
INCLUDING GAITHERSBURG AND
WESTMINSTER.
38 IN ANNAPOLIS.
35 DULLES.
37 MANASSAS.
EVERYONE WILL START AS SNOW COME
TOMORROW MORNING.
FUTURECAST, LET'S GET TO 7 A.M.,
THIS IS THE HEART OF THE MORNING
COMMUTE, WE'VE GOT HEAVY SNOW
JUST ABOUT EVERYWHERE, EVEN
REACHING BALTIMORE BY THEN.
YOU NOTICE THAT PINK AREA,
STARTS TO CREEP TOWARDS
CHARLOTTESVILLE, THAT WILL BE
YOUR MIX.
FOR THE TIME BEING, EARLY
MORNING, THROUGH MID-MORNING
EVERYONE SEES SNOW.
MIX MAKING IT TO FREDERICKSBURG,
CULPEPER BY 10 A.M., WARM AIR
GETS INTO THE METRO BETWEEN NOON
AND 1 P.M.
LUNCHTIME YOU'LL LOOK OUTSIDE.
NOT NECESSARILY SNOW.
KIND OF THE WHITE RAIN AND
TRANSITIONING A BIT.
PINK AREA HOLD ON NORTH AND
WEST.
FIVE O'CLOCK DRAMATIC CHANGE
OVER.
ALL LOOKING AT RAIN.
FREDERICK, THURMONT, HAGERSTOWN,
OVER TO CUMBERLAND DOWN FRONT
ROYAL, WINCHESTER, HIGHER
ELEVATIONS SAW THE EYE LAST WEEK
PROBABLY WILL SEE MORE OF IT.
ALL BE RAIN AT LEAST SOME POINT
BY WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
BY THE TIME THIS TIME TOMORROW
NIGHT POURING RAIN.
THREE CHAP PERS OF LONG WINTER
FORM FOR TOMORROW.
PLANNING FORECAST, THE MORNING
IS SNOW.
HEAVY AT TIMES.
CHANGE OVER TO RAIN.
ONE TO THREE THAT'S LESS SOUTH
AND EAST.
JACKPOT AREA WHERE WE CAN GET
SOME REALLY GOOD SNOW BANDS FIVE
TO EIGHT AND EXTREME
NORTHWESTERN COUNTIES.
SEVEN-DAY FORECAST, SHOWS THAT
EVEN THOUGH THIS WON'T BE FUN,
WE'RE GOING TO GET EVERYTHING
OUT OF HERE MELTED AWAY REAL
QUICK.
BECAUSE THURSDAY WE'VE GOT
SUNSHINE UP TO NEARLY 50
DEGREES.
NOT BAD FRIDAY AS WE HEAD INTO
THE WEEKEND.
SHOWERS IN THE FORECAST.
SATURDAY CHILLY.
LOOK HOW MILD ON SUNDAY.
DRAMATIC, 20 DEGREES IN THE 60S.
THAT WILL FEEL REALLY REALLY
NICE.
DON'T FORGET YOU WANT "FOX5"
WEATHER APP ALL DAY TOMORROW.
HITTING THE ROADS AND
CANCELLATIONS AND DELAYS COMING
THROUGH ON THAT APP, TOO.
>> LIGHT AT THE END OF THE
TUNNEL.
>> SUNDAY LOOKS PRETTY GREAT.
THINK ABOUT SUNDAY TOMORROW ALL
DAY WHEN IT'S AWFUL.
>> THANKS.
>>  STILL TO COME, SIBLINGS
REUNITED.
87-YEAR-OLD WOMAN GETS THE
SURPRISE OF A LIFETIME AND IT'S
ALL CAPTURED ON CAMERA.
>>> ♪ ♪
After months of wearing
only a tiger costume,
we're finally going on the
trip I've been promising.
Because with Expedia,
I saved when I added
a hotel to our flight.
♪
So even when she outgrows
her costume,
we'll never outgrow the memory
of our adventure together.
Unlock savings when
you add select hotels
to your existing trip.
Only when you book
with Expedia.
.
>>> PRESIDENT DONALD TRUMP MADE
OFFICIAL SIGNING THE LAW GIVING
PENTAGON POWER TO START
DEVELOPING NEW BRANCH OF ARMED
FORCES.
PRESIDENT SAID IMPORTANT TO
DEFINE SPACE AN AS WAR FIGHTING
DOMAIN.
AMERICA'S ENEMIES WORKING TO
UNDER NINE U.S. SECURITY THERE.
ONCE ESTABLISHED SPACE FORCE
WILL BE THE SIXTH BRANCH OF
MILITARY.
LAWMAKERS MORE LIKELY TO MAKE IT
A PART OF AIR FORCE.
>>> SUPREME COURT JUSTICE RUTH
BADER GINSBURG IS BACK ON THE
BENCH.
RETURNED EIGHT WEEKS AFTER
UNDERGOING LUNG CANCER SURGERY.
85 YEAR-OLD ON TIME FOR HEARINGS
10 A.M.
WALKED WITHOUT HELP TO HEAR ORAL
ARGUMENT.
VOICE WAS STRONG WHEN SHE ASKED
QUESTIONS.
>> SAD NEWS FROM THE FASHION
WORLD, LEGENDARY DESIGNER CARL
LAGERFELD HAS DIED.
CREATIVE DIRECTOR FOR CHANEL AND
FENDI AND PROLIFIC FIGURE WORKED
UP TILL DEATH.
DESIGNED COLLECTIONS OWN BRAND
AND COLLABORATED WITH H&M.
SICK FOR SEVERAL WEEKS AND MIRED
A NUMBER OF FASHION SHOWS.
CARL LAGERFELD WAS 58 YEARS OLD.
>> GOD BLESS YOU.
>>  EMOTIONAL REUNION IN
PENNSYLVANIA CAPTURED ON CAMERA.
87-YEAR-OLD BETTY NEVER GOT TO
KNOW HER BROTHER.
HE WAS PUT UP FOR ADOPTION AT
JUST THREE MONTHS OLD.
SHE SAYS ALWAYS CURIOUS TO MEET
HIM.
UNSURE IF HE FELT THE SAME WAY.
CHANGED A FEW WEEKS AGO WHEN
GREAT-T-GRANDDAUGHTER DECIDED T
DO DIGGING.
PUT OUT A PLEA FROM HELP ON
SOCIAL MEDIA AND ABLE TO TRACK
HIM DOWN.
>> I FIGURED.
EVEN IF THEY DON'T HAVE MONTHS,
COUPLE YEARS WHATEVER IT IS TO
FINALLY GET TO BE A BIG SISTER
FOR A WHILE, I JUST KNEW THAT
WOULD BE REALLY REWARDING FOR
HER.
SO I WENT OH, MY GOSH, HE WANTS
TO MEET YOU.
SHE JUST LOST IT, NO WAY.
>> I WAS WORRIED BECAUSE I GOT A
PACEMAKER AND I THOUGHT IS THIS
THING GOING TO BE OK IF I SEE
HIM.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHETHER I'D CLUNK
OUT OR WHAT.
>> [LAUGHTER].
>> WHAT A LOVELY PAIR.
>> SHE MET HER BROTHER AT DINER
THIS PAST SATURDAY.
SHE SAID SHE FEELS LIKE A
MISSING PUZZLE PIECE IN PLACE.
>> PACEMAKER TO THE RESCUE.
>> WHEN WE COME BACK FINAL
UPDATE ON WINTER WEATHER.
>> GIRL SCOUTS COOKIE BUSINESS
BOOMING THANKS TO POPULAR ACTOR.
>> ♪ ♪
.
>>> HOW SCHOOL IS THIS.
>> A CLEVER GIRL COULD YOU TELL?
COLORADO TAKING MARKETING TO THE
NEXT LEVEL.
CHARLOTTE HOLME BURG REDESIGNED
THE COOKIE BOX WITH PHOTO OF
JASON MOMOA ON THEM.
CALLED THEM THE MOMOA YOU GET
IT, SHE TOLD REPORTERS MOMS
GETTING REALLY EXCITED AND THEY
ARE SAYING THAT THEY NEED THEM.
>>  SHE'S GOOD AT PR SPIN, TOO.
GOT THE LINES.
>>  SOLD A WHOLE GROUP OF PEOPLE
RIGHT THERE.
>> CAREER AHEAD OF HERSELF.
WELL, YOU CAN EAT GIRL SCOUT
COOKIES HOPEFULLY YOU CAN GET
THEM.
FREE TIME TOMORROW.
>> SIT IN AND EAT, NO DOUBT
ABOUT IT.
ANOTHER CHECK OF EXPECTED
SNOWFALL AMOUNTS FOR TOMORROW.
ALONG 95, THREE TO FIVE BEFORE
WE TRANSITION OVER TO SLEET, ICY
NASTY MIX AND UP NORTH AND WEST
IS MORE JACKPOT AREA.
UP TO FIVE TO EIGHT.
ONE TO THREE SOUTH AND EAST OF
95.
SO GENERALLY THIS WILL FALL
DURING THE MORNING HOURS BEFORE
WE TRANSITION LATE DAY.
SEVEN-DAY FORECAST SHOWS MELTING
AWAY QUICKLY THURSDAY AND
FRIDAY.
AND EVEN BY -- I MEAN LOOK AT BY
SUNDAY, TALKING ABOUT
TEMPERATURES IN THE 60S.
LOOKING PRETTY GOOD THERE BY THE
END OF THE WEEK.
>>  KEEP THINKING ABOUT SUNDAY.
>> IT IS, SO SUE WILL BE ON WITH
THE LATEST AT 9
ANNOUNCER: IT'S TIME TO PLAY
"FAMILY FEUD"! GIVE IT UP FOR