YEAR'T I ND OSH USEWSHEED KI STT
AT
CLD S HLLREFRENTBE T WME T
LD BAN FROMG W TWO  OSOCIS  FEAO
.'S.BED TELM OVE
LEAG H TSIISALPR
NLIT OTSO KIND LEL
W.
IGH
WHSN'TOUGH IAT SG PROBSN'T TOU T
OUGHVEER SOL THEPU OF RVICME
ERSOPACE SOT
ANIO,E HETREHE KNOWIDFRA
WOIHAAVE,IMPLGOG  A M AG.B  H W
AFFIRE H
>>IN
SAL
I
, E.
N SUREOU SNDENRE SEASOEMR.
T T BNYANCH GHESAER AND IT'AT
TOTAM AND I  OUMFI
I AL H A WIT T HA TG.F KHATHEME
TOE I HBEEO IT.
HSUICO KDF
I THEN MERIO
DE DER SUL ARGED.
WH,UNED INVOLD
THIS ANDTING IO
T IAONVEN THAT
IL STAY THISU.
DON'IN HENE TTEOPERATN.
INKO A PCE IN ASTRIMALL T IT WA
TIN T WAS
LEL  DEER
FLORAOL FOR HAMEN
EN ISND THEIDSMEOR
EATOLWORKOKA
SEX CKING
G TO SPERETIRE
TEINSO OEBOO
CO88 BUC
TINTHOME.
>>  STAYENR DISCOUN
Y FOR MEALS RVI A A
ECL  HOLAY
INN  LATNS A OVEHE T
COTRY.IF YOUORE IO
ANHECI.
HOLIY RE BM
RIGHCHCE.."
DON'AL WTITHER O
OFM THI  I DON WTO
TO REM EVER.I MADE THAT CLEAR TE
N'T MAKE
M N SE WANT ER O THER
OF E.
DAPPRECIA EATIVI.TH ONE DOE
EMSR ENE TETIREMENT HOS.
DIFF W TO UTF NG O A
THAT WT STYLES FOR
I'M REA TOS L M MOM.
PRAY SHER O DOT TO HER.
OF MOST DRE
PLACEV.USEDO VOLER A NURSING
HO ANDD TOIO S
SOTIMETHE.
AMILBERE NGRSO T ESEND MRUG,RIG.
WOG ING O TH
T THERE TOND TIM WITH
THRELATIS.
DEESSING EVENHINKIN ABOUT
IT.WHAT AM EXCITEDOUT.
THUY SAI CIN
DIFFERENFOWIFE A IST FUNIONING C
OUND THE US AND
ND C AORDT
TREGREAT.
PLESORKI CLASS FALLYRTABL
KEMO.
OR LONELYOPLE.
HE HAS A CAN KACH
OT ENTERINEDNDL
THE COUNTRY.
>> HEATE TOING A
APP AT LETS REPOR DANROUS
IVERS IN REALTIME.
ASHLEY GRR IS MAD AT
RIGHT BACKT  NOT" WILL B
FLU
> BACKNKE IT OR NOT" WITH B UPDY
MAKI A MURDER FANS.
-EXAMINED BYISCONSIN CIRCU
COURT OFFICIALLY WNING MOTION
AT LEAOT YET. FOUND GUILTYF E MR
OF THERE HAULACK WHO HE
AIMS HE DID NOT KILL. SERVINGIF
PRISON.
AVY'S LAWYER NOW KATHLEEN
ZEILE NE'ER FAMOUS F GETTING
COICTIONS OVERRN.
MAKING APPEAL.
IKE ITR NOT.
>> PART OF JUDICIALSYSTEM.
I FEELIKE I SHE PRESENTED TO
THE COURT THESE XY, REASONS
VALID ENOUGH FOR APPEAL ANOURT
GR EXALY
RUN IT COURSE.KNOW,
IT DID.
IS HAS RUN INTOLL SORTS OF
DEAD ENDS SHE HAS FIGURED OUT
WAY TO TURN IT BACK■ AROUND AND
EP GNG UNTILHE CAN HIT
THIS APPEAL.
THIS DOESN'T RETRY THE CASE.
DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
MEANS CAN B LOOKED AT
POTENTIALLY W KNOWS MAYBE
SEENCE REDUCED OR MAYBE NOT.
AT LEAST FRESH EYES O TS CA
APPELLATE COURT TAKE A SECOND
LOOK AT THIS AND S DURING THE
TRIAL ANY MISS THAT
THE OCESS.Y MAY HAVE SCREWEDP
>> I THINK THE MISNOMER IS
BECAUSE IT GOT NETFLIX SPECIAL
THIS IS WHYT'S HAPPENG.
THAT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
THIS.
>> I THINK I HELP.
>> P POLICE TEE ED.
WHAT IT DOES N DO IS DOES N
WIN QUITTAL, DOES NOT WIN NEW
TRIAL.
>> NO.
>> JUDICIAL SYSTEMN PLACE.
>> PICKED  THE CASE TSHANK T
FIRST DOCUMENTARY.
>> INDEED.SEE HIGH PROFILES.
>> HAD NOT BN A HUGE NATIAL.
>> SECOND WASEALLY ABOUT HER
ALL THE DETECTIVE WORK SHES
DOIN TO TRY TO EXONERATE HIM.
GIANT PR MOVE BY THIS LAER.
SHE GOT INTO THIS POSITION TO D
START TO SH, THOUG
NTASTIC CL PRODUC.
HE DOES MAK CASE HE IS NOT
E GUY.
THAT'S WHY SO EXLLINEN THROUGH
SYSTEM MTIPLE TIMES.XONERATED H.
I DON'T KNOW TT I FEEL LE
THIS SHOULD FINANCE THE W IS
GOIN
>> ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE.
HEARD THE STORIES OFEOPLE WHO
HAVE SERVEDIME BEHIND BARS FOR
LIFE OVER CRIS THEY DIDN'
COMMIT ANDATER RELEASE.
IF THERE'S EVIDENCE AND THERE'S
A T OF QUESTION ABOUT PROCESS.
IF H DIDN'T COMMIT THE CRIME IT
SHOULD BE LOOKED AT
AGAIN I THINK THERE'S STILL A
LOT OF STRONG EVIDENCE TO
SUGGESTHAT HE DI
>> ALSO REQUI US T TAKE A
LOOK THOUSAND THOSE IN CERTA
ECONOMIC BRACKETSON'T ALWAYS
HAVEHE BEST LEGAL DEFENSE FM
THE STARGH
EXTREMELSMART AND HELPS TO ,
MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
DEFINITELY
>> CING UP ATTENTION
PEDESTRIANAND CYCLISTS OH,
YEAH.
I S OUT THERE BABY.
THAPP WHERE YOU CAN RORT
DANGEROUS DRIVERS ME ON THA
AN WORD ON THE CU NEXT.
>>>  ♪
> ♪ ♪
I'a dancer
I live in York City.
I've gotten a t ofork
lastecd
where castg directors will
send me a video of creography
and say, "If you can be here
in a couple hours,
the job is yours."
And th Ieneed my pne to workwhi,
ortreaming
the video they sent me
while I learn the oreograp as .
Th k is to hold
the bar up top and nothe pole,
so tt you have
fu rge of motion.
(VO)
There for you
whent matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now comes with Apple Music on us
and $30Only on Verizon.hones.
DEAREST ITAI
WE LOVE YOU.
MAYBE IT'S YOUR BIG HEARTS.
YOUR SENSE OF STYLE.
WELCOME TO BA100.
(BA100,
YOU'RE CAR FOR TAKE-OFF).
HOW YOU FOLLOW YOUR OWN PATH.
YOU'VE LED REVOLUTIONS...
OF ALL KDS.
YET YOW'T SHOUT ABOUT IT.
'S JUST NN YOUR NATUR
INSTEAD, YOU'LL
QIETLY MA HISTORY.
CAKE.
BEDS.
POETRY.
TROUBLE.
LOVE! HOPE!
D RATHER A LOT OTEA.
THE BEST OBRITAIN,
FROM THE MOMENT
YOU STEP ON BOARD.