ON FOX 5'S "LIKE IT OR NOT" THE
STATE THAT COULD BAN BUYING
CIGARETTES IF YOU'RE NOT AT
LEAST 100 YEARS OLD AND LIAM
NEESON RESPONSE TO ALL THE
BACKLASH HE RECEIVED OVER THE
CONTROVERSIAL COMMENTS.
>>> PLUS, WOULD YOU ACCEPT A
PROMOTION WITH NO RAISE?
IT'S HAPPENING MORE AND MORE.
THOSE STORIES AND MUCH MORE ON
FOX 5'S "LIKE IT OR NOT."
♪ ♪.
>> HELLO, WELCOME TO THE SHOW,
JUST LIKE THE STATE OF THE UNION
CALLS FOR UNITY HERE, OR
HOGWASH.
RIGHT?
>> WE STAND UNITED
>> ARE WE?
ARE WE UNITED ON THIS SHOW THIS
EVENING?
YES, GOOD.
NO SPECIAL GUESTS, WE SHOULD
HAVE BROUGHT SOME IN IN HONOR OF
THE STATE OF THE UNION WHICH IS
STILL A COUPLE HOURS AWAY.
HOW ABOUT THE STATE OF THE DC
SCHOOL SYSTEM?
LET'S GO ON THAT AND FIRE IT UP
WITH THAT TONIGHT
>> SHOULD DC CHARRED SCHOOLS
FOLLOW THE SAME RULES AS
TRADITIONAL PUBLIC SCHOOLS?
THAT QUESTION WAS POSED IN THE
"WASHINGTON POST" TODAY AS A
PETITION IS CIRCULATING CALLING
ON CHARTER SCHOOLS TO BE MORE
TRANSPARENT.
CHARTER SCHOOLS IN THE DISTRICT
ARE FUNDED BY TAXPAYERS BUT
UNLIKE TRADITIONAL PUBLIC
SCHOOLS, THEY ARE PRIVATELY
OPERATED AND THUS INFORMATION
ABOUT HOW FUNDING IS USED IS NOT
EASILY ACCESSIBLE.
UNDER NEW PROPOSED RULES,
CHARRED SCHOOLS, WHICH ARE RUN
BY THEIR OWN BOARDS WOULD THEN
HAVE TO PUBLICIZE WHEN THOSE
BOARDS ACTUALLY MEET.
AND DETAIL HOW THEY PLAN TO
SPEND THE MONIES THAT GIVEN TO
THOSE SCHOOLS.
LET ME SEE THE CHARTER NICK.
"LIKE IT OR NOT"?
>> MAKE THIS QUICK, I'M NOT A
FAN OF CHARTER SCHOOLS AND I
KNOW THAT'S A TOUCHY SUBJECT
WITH A LOT OF PARENTS A.
BECAUSE A LOT OPT FOR CHARTER
SCHOOLS WHEN THEY BELIEVE THE
PUBLIC SCHOOLS ISN'T DOING
EVERYTHING THEY NEED IT TO DO
AND I DON'T BELIEVE THEY'RE THE
SAME WHEN I WENT TO SCHOOL WHEN
WE WERE COMPETITIVE.
I THINK THERE ARE DIFFERENT
STANDARDS IN PUBLIC SCHOOLS AND
IT'S NOT FAIR TO SOME PARENTS
WHO JUST DON'T HAVE THE ABILITY
TO MAY OF TO A NEW NEIGHBORHOOD
AND PUT THEIR KIDS IN SCHOOL.
THAT HAVING BEEN SAID, I THINK
THE TRANSPARENCY IS ALWAYS
BETTER TO KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING,
BUT THE WHOLE PREMISE OF A
CHARTER SCHOOL IS THEY DON'T
HAVE TO OPERATE BY THE RULES
>> IF THE TAXPAYER IS FUNDING
WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING, I DON'T
CARE WHAT DEPARTMENT YOU ARE,
THEN THE TAXPAYER IS OWED THAT.
THEY HAVE BEEN SHOWN EVERYTHING,
THAT MEANS TRANSPARENCY AT ALL
COSTS IF THE TAXPAYER IS PAYING,
I DON'T CARE IF IT'S BEING
OPERATED BY A PRIVATE BOARD, I'M
ENTITLED TO SEE WHAT THEIR
DEALINGS ARE.
AND I UNDERSTAND CHARTER SCHOOLS
WANT LESS RED TAPE AND LESS
BUREAUCRACY, I WANT TO SEE WHAT
YOU'RE DOING
>> DOESN'T SEEM LIKE ANYONE IS
TELL HE THEM HOW TO RUN THE
SCHOOL, IT'S HOW THE MONEY IS
BEING SPENT AND I'M FOR
TRANSPARENCY AND LIKE MARINA
JUST SAID IF TAXPAYER DOLLARS
WILL PAY FOR CHARTER SCHOOLS,
PARENTS AND TAXPAYERS HAVE THE
RIGHT TO KNOW WHERE THAT MONEY
IS BEING SPENT.
>> I'M FOR CHARRED SCHOOLS IN
GENERAL, I LIKE THE IDEA THAT
THE FUTURE OF EDUCATION NOT
EVERYBODY HAS TO LEARN THE EXACT
SAME SET OF THINGS, THAT THERE
ARE INTEREST IN CHILDREN THAT
SHOULD BE FOSTERED THAT KIDS
SHOULD BE GIVEN A HEAD START IF
THEY HAVE ADVANTAGES IN CERTAIN
FIELDS AND THERE'S INTEREST.
I HAVE NO ISSUE WITH THAT.
I'M WITH ALL OF YOU.
TAXPAYER NEEDS TO KNOW WHERE THE
MONEY IS GOING, IF THIS IS A
PRIVATE SCHOOL, THEY CAN HAVE A
PRIVATE SCHOOL AND DO WHATEVER
THEY WANT.
GIVE ME A BREAK, IF I'M PAYING
FOR THE CHARTER SCHOOL TO BE
THERE I CAN'T SHOW UP TO THE
MEETING TO FIND OUT WHERE THE
MONEY IS GOING?
>> I THINK THERE ARE FEWER
PROTECTIONS WITH TEACHERS, THERE
ARE A NUMBER OF ISSUES THAT CAN
BE ASSOCIATED
>> THIS ISN'T A CHARITY, IT'S A
PUBLIC RUN THING, THEREFORE I
WANT TO SEE IT.
>>> FROM SCHOOLS TO WORKPLACE,
WHAT WOULD YOU DO IF YOU WERE
OFFERED A PROMOTION BUT NO
RAISE?
WOULD YOU TAKE IT?
ACCORDING TO THE ARTICLE, ON
CNBC, REFUSALLY 39% OF HR
MANAGERS SAY IT IS COMMON FOR
THEIR COMPANY TO OFFER EMPLOYEE
AS PROMOTION WITHOUT A SALARY
RAISE.
THAT'S A 17 POINTS INCREASE FROM
HR MANAGER WHOSE SAID THE SAME
THING IN 2011, A CAREER EXPERT
TELLING CNBC IT IS A GOOD IDEA
TO TAKE THE PROMOTION, BUT SET
UP A TIMELINE WHEN YOU CAN RE
VISIT THE COMPENSATION.
"LIKE IT OR NOT"
>> I'D RATHER HAVE A PROMOTION
THAN NOT, BUT LIKE A LOT OF
PEOPLE ARE SAYING YOU STILL HAVE
TO ASK FOR RAISE OR ASK FOR
WHATEVER YOU CAN, MAYBE MORE
TIME OFF OR MORE OF WHATEVER YOU
WANT AND SEE IF THEY'RE WILLING
TO NEGOTIATE AND IF THEY DO
VALUE YOU AS AN EMPLOYEE I THINK
THEY WILL FIGURE OUT WAYS TO
MAKE YOU HAPPY AND MEET YOU IN
THE MIDDLE, AS FOR NOT GETTING A
RAISE, THAT IS COMMON, A LOT OF
COMPANIES HAVE SMALL BUDGETS
THEY TRY TO WORK WITH WHAT THEY
HAVE, BUT THE TITLE WILL HELP
YOU GET TO A HIGHER LEVEL OR
BIGGER PAY RAISE LATER WHEN YOU
LEAVE THAT COMPANY, SO I WOULD
SAY HAVE A GOOD ATTITUDE ABOUT
IT AND TAKE IT.
>> YOU GOT TO GET SOMETHING OR
YOUR COMPANY DOESN'T CARE ABOUT
YOU, THEY RECOGNIZE THAT, I
ACTUALLY THINK THAT THIS UPTICK
IS THEY'RE PLAYING ON PEOPLE
AFRAID TO ASK FOR MONEY.
PEOPLE DON'T LIKE TO BE THE ONES
TO ASK FOR A SPECIFIC RAISE.
AND JUST OFFERING IT ONLY
HAPPENS WHEN THERE'S LEVERAGE,
WHEN THEY RECOGNIZE THAT
EMPLOYEE MIGHT LEAVE FOR A
BETTER OPPORTUNITY AND THUS THE
MONEY IS THRUST UPON THEM.
I THINK THIS IS A PSYCHOLOGY
GAME, THERE'S SAYING I KNOW WHEN
YOU WALK IN HERE, YOU WANT
SOMETHING.
BUT I DON'T HAVE TO GIVE YOU
MONEY BECAUSE YOU'RE TOO AFRAID
TO ASK FOR IT
>> BUT ALSO THINKING IT CAN BE A
TRICKY GAME, NO ONE HERE IS
IRREPLACEABLE.
AND I THINK IN THIS BUSINESS YOU
LEARN THAT YOU CAN BE REPLACED.
THEY WILL NEVER GET RID OF ME,
I'M SO-AND-SO.
GUESS WHAT?
YOU KNOW SO-AND-SO GONE NOW.
IT HAPPENS ALL THE TIME.
WE SEE THAT HAPPEN.
I THINK THIS IS ALSO INDICATIVE
OF SOMETHING LARGER, WE'RE
SEEING RECORD JOB NUMBERS, SO
EMPLOYERS ARE NOT HURTING FOR
EMPLOYEES.
>> I LOVE THAT, BY THE WAY
>> PEOPLE ARE WORKING IT'S ONE
OF THOSE THINGS WHERE WE'RE NOT
DESPERATE TO KEEP NICK SMITH BUT
WE CAN JUST THROW EVERYTHING AT
HIM.
NICK, WE DON'T REALLY HAVE MANY
FOR A RAISE RIGHT NOW BUT WE
WOULD LIKE TO OFFER A YOU MORE
RESPONSIBILITY
>> IF THEY SAY HEY, WE WOULD
GIVE YOU A RAISE, WE CAN'T DO IT
RIGHT NOW BUT WE WANT TO GIVE
YOU THIS PROMOTION BECAUSE WE
VALUE YOU, PUTTING IT OUT THERE
WE'RE GIVING YOU THIS PROMOTION,
PERIOD, HAVE A NICE DAY, FORCE
YOU SAY TO GO, BUT WHAT ABOUT
THE MONEY?
AND THAT'S AN UNCOMFORTABLE
CONVERSATION
>> YOU GOT TO WEIGH WHAT THE
PROMOTION WILL DO FOR YOU IN THE
LONG RUN, WILL THIS TRANSLATE
INTO DOLLAR SIGNS DOWN THE ROAD
OR AN EVEN BIGGER PROMOTION, A
BETTER WORK OPPORTUNITY?
ELSE.
THE BOTTOMS LINE IS YOU DON'T
PAY YOUR BILLS WITH SUNSHINE AND
A PROMOTION.
YOU GOT TO MAKE THAT DECISION AT
HOME.
IS THIS WHAT I NEED TO MAKE MY
BOTTOM LINE AND IF YOU DON'T YOU
GOT TO MOVE ON
>> COMING UP.
THE STATE THAT WANTS TO
EVENTUALLY BAN THE SALE OF
CIGARETTES.
LIAM NEESON IS SPEAKING OUT
AFTER THE COMMENTS.
AND A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE CALLING
RACIST AND FELLOW ARMY HAMMER IS
TALKING ABOUT WHITE PRIVILEGE.
A LOT TO GET TO COMING UP ON FOX
5'S "LIKE IT OR NOT."
♪ ♪.
It's time for the Ultimate
Sleep Number Event on the
♪ ♪.
Sleep Number 360 smart bed.
It senses your movement
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
Save 50% on the Sleep Number 360
Limited Edition smart bed.
Plus, 24-month financing
on all smart beds.
Only for a limited time.
[ music playing ]
♪ Here Comes the Sun ♪
You, all of you.
How you live. What you love.
[ laughter ]
That's what inspired us
to create America's
most advanced Internet.
Internet that
puts you in charge.
[ chattering ]
That protects what's important.
That handles everything
[ group cheering ]
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Xfinity.
The future of awesome.
>>>  THAT'S A SEPARATE
CONVERSATION BUT I BELIEVE
THAT'S WHERE THIS IS HEADING.
IT'S IF HAWAII, IT'S AN ESTATE
THAT'S GOT ALL THE OUTDOOR
ACTIVITY, THEY DON'T WANT PEOPLE
SMOKING, THE ONLY PEOPLE THAT
CARE ARE PHILLIP MORRIS AND
THOSE WHO SELL CIGARETTES, CVS
IS NO LONGER TRYING TO SELL,
THERE'S PEOPLE THAT DON'T WANT
IT SELLING AND WANT IT ON IT
>> CIGARETTES IS I THINK ARE
ABSOLUTELY DISGUSTING, I HATE
THE SMELL BUT I DON'T THINK THE
GOVERNMENT SHOULD BE TELLING YOU
THAT YOU CAN'T HAVE CIGARETTES
UNLESS YOU'RE 100 YEARS, I THINK
THAT'S RIDICULOUS, I FIND IT
FASCINATING THERE'S A MOVE TO
BAN CIGARETTES OR CONTINUE TO
RAISE THE AGE OF WHEN YOU CAN
PURCHASE THEM, BUT THEN THERE'S
A MOVEMENT TO LEGALIZE POT.
I DON'T THINK GOVERNMENT SHOULD
TELL YOU, THERE'S SO MANY THINGS
BAD FOR YOU, CELL PHONE CAUSE
CANCER OR ALL OF THESE OTHER
THING WE HEAR HORRIBLE FOR YOUR
HEALTH BUT WE CAN STILL CONSUME
THOSE, SEEMS HYPOCRITICAL
>> I DO WANT TO MEET THE
HUNDRED-YEAR-OLD THAT TAKES UP
SMOKING.
THAT WAITED THAT LONG AND SAID
WHY NOT?
AND IT'S JUST LIKE SUCKER,
SITTING ON THE BEACH IN HAWAII
SMOKING A PACK OF CIGARETTES.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS, I FOUND IT'S
INTERESTING IN POLITICS, SOME
PEOPLE WILL SAY THESE RIDICULOUS
THINGS THAT WILL NEVER ACTUALLY
HAPPEN BUT TO GET ATTENTION TO
IT TO TRY TO GET TO SOME POINT,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHERE THEY WILL
GET TO IT, BECAUSE SELLING
CIGARETTES TO 100-YEAR-OLD
PEOPLE RIDICULOUS, IN THE SAME
WAY PEOPLE SAYING LET'S TAX THE
WEALTH AT 95%, NEVER GOING TO
REALLY DO THAT.
THEY'RE TRYING TO OPEN UP A
CONVERSATION ABOUT SHOULD THE
TAX RATE GO UP?  MAYBE THEY'RE
JUST SAYING THE AGE LIMIT WILL
GO UP BUT NOT TO HE WASN'T.
>> THEY WANT THE CONVERSATION TO
KEEP ON GOING.
>>> LIAM NEESON SPEAKS OUT ABOUT
HIS CONTROVERSIAL COMMENTS'S
WE'LL HEAR FROM HIM NEXT ON FOX
5'S "LIKE IT OR NOT" AFTER THE
BREAK.
♪ ♪.
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
So you finally got Fios, huh?
Yep, and wanna know what the
best part about it is?
Nope.
Gaming with less lag?
Watching movies in 4K?
The best part about it is, right
now,
my mom is streaming classes...
...my dad is streaming games...
And because the fiber-optic
network
gives you insane speed and
capacity...
...they don't have to ask you to
get offline.
Exactly.
You owe me so big time.
100% fiber-optic network.
100% phenomenal.
Switch to Fios Gigabit
Connection
with a 2-year agreement
and get a Netflix premium plan
on us for a year.
>>>  LIAM NEESON HAS BEEN UNDER
FIRE AFTER REVEALING HE ONCE
THOUGHT ABOUT CARRYING OUT A
REVENGE ATTACK AFTER SOMEONE
CLOSE TO HIM WAS RAPED.
NISSAN SAID HE WAS ASHAMED TO
ADMIT HE HAD VIOLENT THOUGHTS
ABOUT KILLING A BLACK PERSON
AFTER HE LEARNED THAT THE
ALLEGED PERSON WAS BLACK.
HE SAID IT TAUGHT HIM A LESSON
ABOUT THE PRIME MALL NEED FOR
REVENGE.
NISSAN WAS ON GOOD MORNING
AMERICA AND HERE'S A PORTION OF
THAT EIGHT-MINUTES INTERVIEW
>> I'M NOT RACIST.
THIS WAS NEARLY 40 YEARS AGO.
>> BUT YOU ASKED ABOUT COLOR.
YOU DIDN'T ASK THE PERSON WAS
TALL, SHORT, BIG OR SMALL.
>> I DID, ACTUALLY, I ASKED ALL
THOSE QUESTIONS, I DID.
BUT I DID ASK ABOUT RACE, YES.
>> BECAUSE AT LEAST WHAT WE
HEARD AND SAW, IT WAS ONLY
ASKING ABOUT COLOR.
WOULD YOU HAVE HAD THE SAME
REACTION IF YOUR FRIEND HAD SAID
IT WAS A WHITE MAN.
>> DEFINITELY.
IF SHE SAID IRISH OR SCOTT OR
BRIT I WOULD HAVE SAID THE SAME
FACT.
I WAS TRYING TO DO HONOR STAND
UP FOR MY DEAR FRIEND, AND THIS
TERRIBLE MID, EVIL FASHION
>> AS WE WALKED OUT ONSET HE HUG
YOUED THE BLACK AUDIENCE MEMBERS
AND THAT'S DRAWN A LOT OF
ATTENTION, NISSAN'S NEW
COMMENTS.
"LIKE IT OR NOT"
>> I'M ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE A
YEAR AGO I KNOW THEY WILL ADD ME
BUT I LIKE TAKEN, I LIKE LIAM
NEESON I WANT TO BELIEVE THIS
GUY IS SOMEONE I THINK A LOT OF
OLD PEOPLE MISSPOKE AND THEY
DON'T NECESSARILY HAVE THE
LANGUAGE TO ARTICULATE WHAT THEY
WANT TO SAY, I DON'T SEE LIAM
NEESON SOMEONE WALKING THROUGH
THE STREETS OF CHARLOTTESVILLE
CARRYING THE TIKI TORCH
>> HE SAID HE WENT OUT TO BLACK
NEIGHBORHOOD TO SEE IF HE COULD
START A FIGHT.
HE REALLY WANTED TO COMMIT AN
ACT OF VIOLENCE.
I KNOW IT WAS 40 YEARS AGO.
THIS GUY IS A FREAK.
IT'S DISTURBING.
>> I'M JUST GOING TO LET IT SIT
THERE.
I DON'T WANT TO BE IN A POSITION
TO DEFEND HIM.
I THINK THERE ARE EXAMPLES OF
MUCH MORE EGREGIOUS BEHAVIOR
THAN THAT OF LIAM NEESON.
THAT'S JUST ME
>> WOW.
BIGGER THAN THE REST OF US.
THAT IS A REALLY UNUSUAL STORY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY HE TOLD
THAT STORY.
>> LIKE HE'S PROUD OF IT
>> HE'S LIKE I UNDERSTAND THIS
CHARACTER BECAUSE I WENT THROUGH
SOMETHING LIKE IT.
I WANTED TO BEAT UP A COMPLETE
STRANGER
>> BECAUSE
>> BECAUSE OF THE COLOR OF SKIN,
WAIT A MINUTE.
LIKE, I UNDERSTAND THE IDEA OF
RETRIBUTION, I REMEMBER WHEN
THAT CRAZY PERSON UP AT MICHIGAN
STATE WHO FONDLED ALL THE
GYMNAST, WHEN HE WAS IN COURT
AND THE DAD GOT UP IN FRONT OF
THE JUDGE ONE OF THE DAD'S AND
SAID, I'D LIKE TO HAVE FIVE
MINUTES WITH HIM, YOUR HONOR?
AND THEN LUNGED AT HIM.
THAT RESONATED WITH EVERYBODY.
HE WANTED TO GET THAT GUY FOR
THE HORRIBLE THINGS THAT THAT
GUY DID.
THE IDEA OF WALKING AROUND A
NEIGHBORHOOD BECAUSE SOMETHING
HAPPENED TO SOMEBODY YOU LOVE
AND JUST BEAT ANYBODY UP OVER
IT, TO ME, MAKES NO SENSE.
>> I WONDER TOO, IF PARTIALLY
THIS IS, HONESTLY AS AN
AFRICAN-AMERICAN WE HAVE HAD TO
LEARN TO NAVIGATE SPACES.
WE KNOW THAT THE ZIMMERMANS ARE
OUT THERE, TODAY IS TRAYVON
MARTIN'S 24TH BIRTHDAY WOULD
HAVE BEEN.
THAT RESONATES, THAT'S ALL
THAT'S BEEN ON BLACK TWITTER,
WE'RE VERY AWARE THIS HAPPENS.
I'M AWARE THERE ARE PEOPLE LIKE
LIAM WHO LOOK AROUND LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING TO START WITH MEN OF
COLOR, IT'S UP TO ME TO NAVIGATE
THAT.
I DON'T HAVE THE LUXURY OF THE
BENEFIT OF THE DOUBT TO MOVE IN
THE SAME SPACE AS LOT OF WHITE
MEN DO WITHOUT BEING SOMEHOW
EITHER THE CAUSE OF OR SUSPECTED
OF BEING CAUSE OF.
THAT'S WHY IT'S UNCOMFORTABLE
FOR ME.
I THINK HANDLED THIS REALLY
WELL-BEING EXTREME DIPLOMATIC.
I WALK AROUND PROTECTED I'M
AWARE SOMETHING TO CAPE AT ANY
TIME.
WHAT WON'T HAPPEN IS I DON'T
WANT TO BE A VICTIM BECAUSE LIAM
WAS LOOKING FOR SOMEONE TO A
BLACK BASTARD.
>> IT'S OK FOR YOU TO BE MAD
ABOUT THIS
>> IT'S UNCOMFORTABLE.
I WANT TO BE BETTER THAN THAT.
DOES THAT MAKE SENSE.
>> I WILL SAY SOMETHING, ONE
THING I TOOK AWAY FROM THIS, THE
WAY THAT ROBIN ROBERTS HANDLED
THIS INTERVIEW AND SHE HAD EVERY
RIGHT TO BE ABSOLUTELY OUTRAGED
BY THE COMMENTS AND SHE WAS JUST
SO PERFECT AT HAVING A
CONVERSATION WITH HIM.
>> TRYING TO AT LEAST HAVE A
CONVERSATION.
>> OK.
WELL, MOVING ON TO ANOTHER
ACTOR.
ARMY HAMMER HE RECENT STANDARD
ON BASIS OF SEX AND GOT A GOLDEN
GLOBE NOMINATION CALL ME BY YOUR
NAME MEANWHILE HE'S WORKED HARD
TO GET WHERE HE IS, IT WOULD BE
WRONG OF HIM TO NOT THINK HE'S
BENEFITTED FROM HAVING WHITE
PRIVILEGE.
HE TOLD THE BRITISH GQ THERE ARE
WHITE PEOPLE WHO EXERCISE THEIR
WHITE PRIVILEGE WITH OR WITHOUT
KNOWING IT AND I WOULD BE
FOOLISH TO SIT HERE AND SAY THAT
HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH MY CAREER
AND I CAN'T SIT HERE AND SAY
THAT BUT ALSO PEOPLE MUST BE
AWARE OF THE WORK ETHIC IT
TAKES, WHAT DO WE THINK ABOUT
ARMY SAID?
BRAM?
"LIKE IT OR NOT."
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS ONE.
THE WAY I DON'T UNDERSTAND LIAM
NEESON'S STORY, HE'S PLAYING
RUTH BADER GINSBURG'S HUSBAND
FROM THE 1950's, WHO HAPPENED TO
BE A WHITE GUY.
SO YOU KNOW, LIKE MICHAEL
BJORDAN ISN'T GETTING THAT ROLE,
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH WHITE
PRIVILEGE IN THE SAME WAY HE
WASN'T GOING TO BE IN BLACK
PANTHER.
THIS IS A GOOD LOOKING, TALENTED
GUY.
DID HE GET?
BECAUSE HE'S WHITE?
I GUESS IF HE WANTS TO BELIEVE
THAT, FINE.
I DON'T THINK I'M SITTING IN
THIS CHAIR RIGHT NOW BECAUSE OF
SOME KIND OF PRIVILEGE.
PERSONALLY.
BUT MAYBE I'M WRONG FOR THINKING
THAT WAY.
ASK MY EMPLOYER, I GUESS.
>> HE GOT THIS TOTAL HOLLYIER
THAN THAW.
I'M NOT A MILLENNIAL, EVEN
THOUGH HE'S A MILLENNIAL, I
WOULD NEVER HAVE A SELFIE AND
POST IT AFTER HE DIED BECAUSE
THAT IS SO NARCISTIC AND NOW I'M
HERE BECAUSE I'M WHITE.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
WHO ARE YOU?
AND WHAT IS GOING THROUGH YOUR
BRAIN.
>> IT'S ARROGANT, I'VE HAD MEN
DESCRIBE THEIR WHITE PRIVILEGE
TO ME I'M LIKE REALLY TELL ME
MORE ABOUT THAT, ABUNDANCE,
JAY-Z, CARDI B ALL OF THESE
FAMOUS PEOPLE OF COLOR HAVE A
LOT OF WHITE PRIVILEGE TOO.
I THINK THERE'S RICH PRIVILEGE.
I THINK THERE'S ATTRACTIVENESS
PRIVILEGE, I THINK THOSE HELP
YOU IN LIFE
>> BUT THE COLOR OF YOUR SKIN I
DON'T THINK, ESPECIALLY IN 2019
THAT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
WHERE YOU'RE AT.
IT'S ABOUT DEDICATION AND TIME
YOU PUT IN
>> THERE'S A LOT OF WHITE PEOPLE
DON'T GET MOVIE JOB
>> AND A LOT OF PEOPLE OF COLOR
BUSTING THEIR YOU KNOW WHAT JUST
TO PAY THE BILLS, COME ON.
>>> ATTENTION DRIVERS, DC MIGHT
BE BANNING MORE RATE TURNS ON
RED LIGHTS, IS THIS A GOOD IDEA?
FOX 5'S "LIKE IT OR NOT" WILL BE
RIGHT BACK.
♪ ♪.
People aren't talking
about how much
money they saved
buying Giant Brand Chicken.
They're not talking
about how our
pre-chopped veggies are
perfect time-savers.
They're also not talking
about our unique assortment
of over 1,300 Nature's
Promise Items.
Or our fresh grab and
go salads and sandwiches.
They're not talking,
because they're eating.
Oh hello, that
looks so good.
At Giant, it's the little
things that make
meal time easy,
so you have more time with
the people you love.
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>>  BACK ON FOX 5'S "LIKE IT OR
NOT."
IF YOU FIND YOURSELF AT A LIGHT
AND ITCHING TO MAKE THE RIGHT
TURN TO GET HOME TO SAY, I DON'T
THINK WATCH US, DON'T DO IT
BECAUSE YOU'LL BE IN TROUBLE AS
DC IS REPORTEDLY MOVING TO BAN
RIGHT TURNS ON RED LIGHTS AT
ANOTHER 100 INTERSECTIONS BY
JULY.
THE DEPARTMENT OF TRANSPORTATION
SAID THE GOAL HERE IS TO MAKE
ROADS SAFER.
AAA MIDATLANTIC THINK THEY'RE
CRA, CRA.
THEY BELIEVE RESTRICTING DRIVERS
ON RIGHT TURNS INCREASES RISKS
CARS HITTING PEDESTRIANS AND
LIKELY WILL CAUSE A LOT MORE
REAR END ACCIDENTS.
RIGHT MOVE MARINA?
"LIKE IT OR NOT"
>> IF IT'S GREEN WE GO, IF IT'S
YELLOW YOU HIT THE GAS IF IT'S
RED YOU LOOK BOTH WAYS AND YOU
GO IN MIAMI, YOU ALWAYS GO RIGHT
TURN ON RED.
IT'S 100 INTERSECTIONS.
THERE'S A LOT.
I KNOW THIS WORKS IN NEW YORK
CITY BECAUSE YOU GOT SO MUCH
PEDESTRIAN TRAFFIC, OBVIOUSLY
THE DISTRICT HAS A LOT OF PEOPLE
ON FOOT.
THEY WANT TO AVOID HITTING
PERSON TO THE RIGHT IF YOU'RE
TURNING YOU'RE IN THE
INTERSECTION BLOCKING THE
CROSSWALK.
MAYOR BOWSER HAS A VISION ZERO
PLAN, SHE WANTS ZERO PEDESTRIAN
FATALITIES BY THE YEAR 2024 AND
THAT'S AN AMBITIOUS PLAN.
SHE'LL HAVE TO DO SOMETHING, SHE
IS NOT DRIVING THE CARS CAUSING
THE CRASHES, WHAT DO YOU DO?
YOU IMPLEMENT MEASURES LIKE
THIS.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW IF THIS IS
SOME SORT OF MONEY GRAB.
WILL THEY HAVE CAMERAS AND
WATCHING AND TICKETING PEOPLE,
WE KNOW ABOUT THE SPEED CAMERAS
ALREADY AND I ALWAYS BELIEVE
THERE'S SOME SORT OF MONEY
SITUATION THAT ALIGNS.
I HEAR BOTH SIDES, I'M NOT SURE
HOW I FEEL
>> I HAD A CHANCE TO HIT THE
STREET TO TALK TO PEOPLE BECAUSE
ONE OF THE THINGS PEOPLE ON THE
STREET WANT TO KNOW IS, HEY,
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
NICK, IF THE IDEA IS TO MAKE NO
RIGHT TURNS ON RED, WILL IT MAKE
US SAFER?
WORD ON THE CURB.
>> I MEAN, IF IT'S SAFETY ISSUE,
I GUESS THE MAKES SENSE BUT
HONESTLY, I HATE THE IDEA.
I'VE BEEN ABLE TO MAKE A RIGHT
ON RED
>> I HAVEN'T GIVEN IT A WHOLE
LOT OF THOUGHT
>> YOU ARE IN FAVOR
>> ALL IN FAVOR
>> SAID FROM THE AAA THAT IT'S
NOT GOING TO HELP ANYTHING
>> PEDESTRIANS MIGHT TRY TO BEAT
THE LIGHT THEMSELVES, SPRINT
ACROSS OR GO WHEN THEY'RE NOT
ALLOWED TO
>> IT WOULD GIVE THEM TO PAY
ATTENTION TO THE PEDESTRIANS A
LITTLE BIT MORE.
>> WHAT I'D LIKE IS FOR DRIVERS
PROBABLY AND SOME WALKERS TO BE
MORE CONSCIOUS ANXIOUS
>> THEY FORGET THAT ONCE THEY
GET OUT OF THE CAR, THEY BECOME
A PEDESTRIAN
>> IT'S BOUND TO CAUSE SOME
CONFUSION AT BEST.
BECAUSE WE'RE CREATURES OF
HABIT.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO GET STUCK AT
A RED LIGHT WITH HER AND HAVE A
CONVERSATION WITH HER
>> SO MUCH MORE INTELLIGENT THAN
US REGULAR FOLKS
>> WHAT'S WRONG WITH TURNING ON
RIGHT?
WHEN DID TO BECOME AN ENORMOUS
ISSUE
>> THEY ROLL AND HIT PEOPLE.
THAT'S OBVIOUSLY WHAT THE
PROBLEM IS.
>> THAT'S ALREADY A CRIME YOU DO
HAVE TO STOP ON A RED LIGHT.
THERE'S NO -- THAT'S NEVER
CHANGED.
IT'S MY UNDERSTANDING THAT THE
ENTIRE THING WAS A FALL LISTSY.
IT WAS IMPLEMENTED IN THE 70's
STOPPING AT RED LIGHTS SOMEHOW
WOULD SAVE GAS AND THAT'S NOT
NECESSARILY TRUE.
>> I DON'T HAVE A CAR AND I WALK
TO WORK EVERY DAY AND I ALSO
THAT PEOPLE ARE AGGRESSIVE AT
THE RED LIGHT RIGHT TURN, THEY
THINK IT'S THEIR RIGHT TO BE IN
THE THE MIDDLE OF THE
INTERSECTION, IF YOU'RE ON A
BIKE, SCOOTER OR WALKING, THEY
TRY TO ZIP PAST YOU, I CAN SEE
WHY IT WOULD BE NECESSARY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE FATAL
RATES ARE.
I DON'T KNOW IF ANY OF YOU KNOW.
IF IT'S A SERIOUS PROBLEM AND
PEOPLE ARE GETTING HURT OR
KILLED THEN YES
>> THE SCOOTER SITUATION IS
TERRIBLE.
SOMETHING NEEDS TO BE DONE TO
REGULATE THEM.
PEOPLE ARE FLYING OUT ACROSS
LIGHTS
>> YOU THINK ABOUT CROSSWALKS,
RED LIGHTS, LIAM NEESON SLIDE UP
IN THE D M's, HAVE A GOOD NIGHT
EVERYBODY.
♪ ♪.
[CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
WARNER BROS. D