[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> NOW WE KNOW YOU GUYS
PROBABLY HAVE SO MUCH CATCHING
UP TO DO.
A LOT OF TALK.
SO WE'RE GOING TO SEND YOU OUT
TO LUNCH TOGETHER, BUT RIGHT NOW
YOU CAN READ BRANDI'S FULL STORY
IN THE MARCH ISSUE OF "REAL
SIMPLE" MAGAZINE.
>> YOU CAN WATCH THE REST OF THE
REUNION ON OUR FACEBOOK PAGE.
HAVE A GREAT DAY BECAUSE WE ARE.
YES.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪♪
Woman:
Jason Morgan?
You're Jason Morgan,
right?
Hi, I'm Harmony.
Welcome to Beechers Corners.
Thank you.
Is this
your first visit?
No.
Oh.
Well, since you called with
questions about Dawn of Day,
I suspect you want to know
what's up with us, right?
Check us out?
So, let's get to it.
♪♪
Thank you
for meeting me.
Yeah, of course.
Thanks for the...invite.
[ Sighs ]
Although I think I know
why you invited me here.
Yes.
Jason told me
about the "breakup,"
and I just wanted to offer
my support to both of you.
Which means you want to talk me
out of breaking up with him.
[ Laughs ]
-Hey.
Sorry to interrupt.
I just wanted to say "hi."
Drew. Hi.
Hi.
Hi, yourself.
Josslyn told me
the good news about Oscar...
What? What?
There's good news about Oscar?
Yeah, uh, the -- the --
the tumor hasn't grown,
so it buys him
more time.
What?
That is --
That's incredible.
Anyway, uh,
his mom and I,
we're trying to get back
to normal life.
[ Chuckles ]
Whatever that is.
So, I finally have time to check
in on Hank or Shiloh --
Shi-S-Shiloh.
No, don't --
don't even worry
about it. I got --
Well, hold on.
If -- If Drew has the time...
I mean, the more information,
the better, right?
Exactly.
And I want to help,
so...
He made a point
to be "friendly,"
so the least I could do
is be "friendly" back.
♪♪
-Hey. I-It was --
-Yeah.
It was good to see you,
and -- and I'm --
I'm really happy
to hear about Oscar.
Yeah. Me, too.
Thanks.
♪♪
Hey.
Let's hope
we get lucky
and Drew gets
leverage on Shiloh,
and then you and Jason won't
have to break up after all.
You're Dr. Neil Byrne.
And you're Alexis Davis.
♪♪
Yep.
Says it right here.
"Dr. Neil Byrne.
Psychiatrist."
Gee, I wish I had read this
before I pocketed it.
I wish I had known I was
inviting a patient to dinner.
So what do we do now?
Well, that's up to you.
♪♪
[ Dramatic music plays ]
Do you see a spot
for Kiki's memorial brick?
Yeah, near the, uh --
the flower bed down there.
She'd like that...
♪♪
If you have postmenopausal
osteoporosis
and a high risk for fracture
now might not be the best time
to ask yourself
are my bones strong?
Life is full of make-or-break
moments.
That's why it's so important
to help reduce your risk of
fracture with Prolia®.
Only Prolia® is proven to help
strengthen
and protect bones from fracture
with 1 shot every 6 months.
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take
XGEVA®.
Serious allergic reactions,
like low blood pressure; trouble
breathing;
throat tightness; face, lip, or
tongue swelling;
rash; itching; or hives have
happened.
Tell your doctor about dental
problems
as severe jaw bone problems may
happen
or new or unusual pain in your
hip groin, or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone fractures
have occurred.
Speak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects,
like low blood calcium, serious
infections,
which could need
hospitalization, skin problems,
and severe bone, joint, or
muscle pain.
Are you ready?
Ask your doctor how Prolia® can
help strengthen your bones.
In our family
we love tiny things.
We save every drop of rain,
study every bite of frost.
Because caring for tiny things
can make a mighty impact.
Ocean Spray.
Act Tiny,
Be Mighty.
Farmer Owned
Since 1930.
Don't let your longwear
weigh you down.
New Infallible Fresh Wear
Foundation by L'Oreal.
Get longwear coverage
from our most lightweight,
breathable formula.
Defies sweat and transfer.
Stays fresh. Feels light.
All day to night.
New Infallible Fresh Wear
by L'Oreal.
Oh milk. Am I willing to pay
the price for loving you?
You'll make my morning, but
ruin my day.
Complicated relationship with
milk?
Pour on the Lactaid, 100% real
milk,
just without that annoying
lactose.
Mmm, that's good.
I use this
every day
But is Beth's soap
as clean rinsing as Dove?
My soap's still leaving
plenty of things behind
But Dove is cleaner rinsing
My soap,
...Dove.
Made with 1/4
moisturizing cream...
Dove cleans and cares
beautifully.
The G.H. community
meant a lot to Kiki.
It's a very thoughtful
gesture...
♪♪
I didn't
see you there --
[ Door opens ]
Griffin?
Come away from there,
would you?
You're -- You're too close
to the edge.
You have some kind
of death wish?
Wouldn't want you
to lose your balance.
What brings you here?
Looking for Griffin?
No, I'm looking for you.
I know what you've been up to.
♪♪
We can do whatever
you feel is best...
Uh, I'm happy to give you
a referral.
Well, I can't very well
go back to Dr. Collins
because I'm representing
his wife in his divorce...
And there,
I did it again.
I offered way
too much information.
You're talking to a therapist.
There's no such thing.
But I-I can tell
you're uncomfortable.
So, I am going
to give you
the name of
an associate who may...
[ Paper tears ]
...be a good fit.
And -- And I hope
it works out
between you
and Dr. Sautner.
Thank you.
Uh, good night.
♪♪
[ Sighs ]
[ Sighing ] Oh, God.
That's a nice surprise.
Well, you know,
I had a free night.
I thought maybe we could,
uh, reconnect...
That's great, man.
Thanks, uh --
Thanks for calling.
After you.
-Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.
-[ Sighs ]
You know, I, uh...
[ Door closes ]
...really wanted to,
uh, you know,
talk about our time
in Afghanistan together.
I guess that's back when
you went by Hank, right?
[ Chuckles ]
Well, it's, uh...
it's true.
You, uh --
You saved my life.
But, uh -- But it was
more than that, man.
We, uh -- We were
seriously tight.
Although, you, uh --
you held your cards a little
closer to the vest than I did.
You sure as hell
held your liquor better.
There was, uh,
no drunken, sloppy,
late-night confessions
from you.
Take it there were
from you?
Well, you know, just things
that I had to get off my chest.
In case I didn't make it back
that day, you know?
Yeah, well,
that's understandable.
[ Chuckles ]
I mean, you always said that you
didn't remember, but, uh...
I think you were doing that
just to make me feel better.
Must have been...
some confessions.
♪♪
How are Danny
and Scout?
Scout -- she is
gonna be two...
Oh, my gosh.
...in like two weeks.
[ Laughs ]
And Danny, he's just
the sweetest,
most thoughtful little boy
in the whole entire world.
Mm.
I actually told him I was coming
here to see you and Sonny,
and -- I'm sorry, I don't have
a purse, it's in my pocket --
but he, um,
wanted me to give you this.
Oh!
[ Laughs ]
Isn't it cute?
Oh, my goodness.
It's so adorable.
[ Gasps ] Wow.
Little boys can surprise you,
can't they?
Um...
I mean,
I would never associate
Danny with
crafts and cards.
I mean, that boy, he's such
a little adventure guy.
[ Chuckling ]
Oh, tell me about it.
He's, like, running and
jumping and everything.
I know. I know. I just had
to have Monica lock the attic
because he was bringing
Annabelle the Second
up to the attic and
they were playing on the roof.
Who does that
sound like, huh?
Just like his father.
I mean, just
fearless enough
to where you want
to rip your hair out, but...
just sweet and thoughtful
all at the same time.
You're gonna have
to work a little harder
to hide how much
you love Jason
if you want to sell
this whole breakup thing.
But before I answer
your questions,
do you mind answering
one of mine?
Uh, depends
on the question.
You're here
on someone's behalf.
Who?
A family member?
I consider her one,
yes.
In Beechers Corners?
Is it someone I know?
No.
Well, then,
why come here?
Why not just talk to Shiloh?
He's in Port Charles.
Because I wanted to talk
to someone besides...
Hank Archer.
[ Laughs ]
Now that's a blast
from the past.
[ Chuckles ]
I used to be
called Lorraine.
Yeah, me,
a "Lorraine."
My parents chose it,
obviously,
but it was
never a good fit.
I found it so freeing
and empowering
to be able to choose
my own name.
So, you became Harmony.
Like Hank became Shiloh.
Well, choosing my own name
was a-a bridge
to becoming my true self.
Shiloh.
[ Chuckles ]
He untethered me from
what was holding me back,
and Dawn of Day
opened my mind
and my heart
to my own potential.
♪♪
Did you notice that community
center across the street?
Shiloh and I built it
from the ground up.
Are you still in touch
with, uh -- with Shiloh?
Yeah, well...of course.
We still conduct business
together,
if that's what you mean.
But you're not together.
I mean, you're here.
Shiloh's in Port Charles.
Why?
♪♪
MOVING?
THAT'S HARDER NOW BECAUSE
OF PSORIATIC ARTHRITIS.
BUT YOU'RE STILL MOVED
BY MOMENTS LIKE THIS.
DON'T LET PSORIATIC
ARTHRITIS TAKE THEM AWAY.
TALTZ REDUCES JOINT
PAIN AND STIFFNESS
AND HELPS STOP THE
PROGRESSION OF JOINT DAMAGE.
FOR PEOPLE WITH
MODERATE TO
SEVERE PSORIASIS,
90% SAW SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT.
TALTZ EVEN GIVES YOU A CHANCE
AT COMPLETELY
CLEAR SKIN.
DON'T USE IF YOU'RE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING, YOU SHOULD
BE CHECKED FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR
ABILITY TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU
HAVE AN INFECTION, SYMPTOMS,
OR RECEIVED A
VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INFLAMMATORY BOWEL DISEASE
CAN HAPPEN WITH TALTZ,
INCLUDING WORSENING OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
FOR ALL THE THINGS
THAT MOVE YOU.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
Gentle means everything,
so we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients
Added one handed pumps
And beat the
top safety standards
The new JOHNSON'S®
Choose Gentle
This is nice.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is nice.
Mmmm how did you make the
dip so rich and creamy?
Oh, it's a Philadelphia-
-Family Recipe.
Can I see it?
No.
New Philadelphia Dips.
So good,
you'll take all the credit.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Voluptuous Volume.
Intense Length.
Feathery-Soft Lashes.
This is what
paradise looks like.
Lash Paradise Mascara
from L'Oréal Paris.
Take your lashes to paradise.
90% of women
have a skincare routine.
But what about a
lip care routine?
Pay your lips some attention.
The ChapStick Total
Hydration Collection.
Exfoliate
Nourish
Naturally enhance
your lips.
ChapStick.
Put your lips first.
You can't put a price on love.
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
Ever notice how hard it is to
clean impossible kitchen and
bathroom messes with wipes
and spray cleaners?
Try Mr. Clean Magic Eraser.
Just add water, squeeze,
and erase.
Mr. Clean Magic Eraser works
great
on burnt-on food in the
kitchen.
It's perfect for cleaning
stubborn bathroom soap scum.
Even on glass.
And it even removes four times
more permanent marker per swipe.
Try Mr. Clean Magic Eraser,
for your impossible kitchen and
bathroom messes.
Emerge Restored,
Replenished,
Fortified.
Emerge everyday with Emergen-C.
Packed with B vitamins,
Electrolytes, Antioxidants,
Plus more vitamin C than
10 oranges.
Why not feel this good
every day?
Emerge and See.
I don't understand. What is it
you think I'm "up to"?
Oh, come on, Kevin. It's why
you're up here, isn't it?
I went to your office,
looking for you.
I found this
on your desk.
♪♪
You've arranged for
a commemorative brick
in Kiki's honor.
The letter says that
the best way to choose a spot
is to look down
from the roof,
so I-I came up here
to see for myself,
give you my input...
It's a lovely gesture, Kevin.
Thank you.
It's all
I could think of.
Just have something of Kiki
here at the hospital,
and maybe bring
some small comfort
to the people
who miss her.
I was just saying
the same thing.
Let me know when, uh,
you guys pick the final spot.
I'm sorry.
I, uh...
I have somewhere
I need to be.
♪♪
Now Kiki will be
a part of the place
that she loved forever.
I admit,
a brick isn't much,
but if it dissipates
your anger towards me,
then I'm doubly glad
I thought of it.
I'm not angry, Kevin.
I jumped to conclusions.
I owe you an apology.
♪♪
See, in order to find out
more about Shiloh,
I have to make myself
seem really vulnerable.
Okay, but this guy
obviously has charisma,
and he knows
how to use it...
Do you think
he's a sexual predator?
Well, I intend
to find out.
Not only
for Kristina's sake,
but every other girl
that's living under that roof.
That's why I have
to see this through.
Okay. But to do that,
you have to con him, right?
Do you think you can?
Trust me.
Shiloh's about to get
a taste of his own medicine.
I was one of Shiloh's
earliest supporters.
He was the visionary,
and I was the pragmatist
to help make it work.
So, why are
you guys apart?
That's simple -- he wants
to expand the work that we do.
Okay,
so why Port Charles?
Well, the city suffered
a bad earthquake a while back,
and Shiloh found people
in Port Charles
who needed
the kind of outreach
that Dawn of Day
could provide.
So, he left,
and I stayed behind
to continue the work
that we do here.
Yeah, he seems, uh,
pretty devoted to his work.
What about a life
outside of it?
Shiloh's life
is his work.
Oh, so no -- no family?
No -- No interest in --
in having a family?
[ Chuckles ]
Dawn of Day is a family.
Why do you ask?
Well, because [sighs]
the young lady
I'm here for,
I mean, she's really involved
with Dawn of Day,
but she's -- you know,
she's a little naive,
and she's growing
attached to Shiloh
as more than a mentor.
I'm s--
What are you implying?
She's falling for him.
So, h-how does he --
how does he handle
situations like this
when they come up?
♪♪
Yeah, well, that's the, uh --
the thing about confessions.
When you're in the middle
of making them,
they seem of
monumental importance.
But, uh, when you're
looking at them in the
grand scheme of life,
well, they're not important
at all, are they?
I guess you got a point,
but, uh, you know,
why are you still
thinking about them?
I don't know. I mean, I guess
coming back to Port Charles,
it just, you know, brought it
all back, you know?
First,
I run into a brother
that I didn't even know you have
with your face.
Yeah.
Right? And then
I-I see you again
with -- with --
with a-another face,
and -- and you don't know me
from Adam, you know, so...
Well, I don't remember
anyone or anything,
so, uh, don't take it
personally.
Not at all.
So, is there any chance
your memories will return?
♪♪
-We're doing karaoke later,
and you're gonna sing.
-Jamie, this is your house?
-I know, it's not much,
but it's home.
Right, kids?
-Kids?
-Papa, Papa!
-[ Laughs ]
-You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
-Oh, yeah.
-This one is tiny like a child.
-Yeah, she is.
Oh, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most --
a home and auto bundle
from Progressive.
-Oh, sweetie,
please, play for us.
-Oh, no, I couldn't.
-Please.
-Okay.
[ Singing in Spanish ]
There's little rest
for a single dad,
and back pain made it hard to
sleep and get up on time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid,
plus the 12 hour pain
relieving strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a Better AM.
This is Charlie not coughing
because he took Delsym 12-hour.
And this is Charlie still not
coughing
while trying his hardest not to
wake Zeus.
Delsym 12-hour.
Nothing lasts
longer for powerful
cough relief.
Advanced Génifique Serum
activates signs
of youthful-looking skin.
Fine lines appear reduced.
Skin is more radiant,
looks visibly younger
in only four weeks.
Love Your Age.
Customize your
free gift at Macy's.
The Beauty Destination.
At Children's National,
Customize your
free gift at Macy's.
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
[phone ringing]
Remember the way we
used to do things?
Hey man...
Like connect with friends?
Dig it!
Or get in shape?
Or sell a house
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
[crash]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
♪ Keep your feet
from coming off the ground ♪
[ Clanging ]
[ Wrench clatters ]
♪♪
♪ Step in line and move along ♪
[ Grunts ]
♪ I said, all right,
I'm getting home ♪
♪ We paint a line ♪
♪ And set the course ♪
[ Knock on door ]
♪ We pass on by
and through the door ♪
♪ And the thought
occurs to me ♪
Sasha.
Mind if I come in?
Uh, sure.
♪♪
I was in town visiting Nina
and thought I'd stop by.
I hope
that's all right.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Uh...
It's been a while.
Not since
Kiki's funeral...
♪ Keep your feet
from coming off the ground ♪
I can't imagine what
you've been going through.
♪ Live each moment ♪
It must be so hard walking past
Kiki's apartment every day...
How are you doing?
♪ Take it in
before it turns to memory ♪
Want to know
how I'm doing?
I'm sick and tired
of everybody talking to me
about Kiki.
Talking isn't gonna
bring her back.
♪ Don't get lost
and lose the here ♪
Once I calmed down,
I realized --
that you weren't
protecting Franco.
You didn't notify the
police because you knew
he wasn't a threat,
and if you thought he was, you
definitely would've warned us.
I never believed
Franco would harm anyone.
Especially not
your beautiful daughter...
Even with
his dark side,
I never thought he would act
on those impulses.
I know.
I spoke with him.
I'm convinced
he's innocent.
That means the killer
is still free.
That is a real problem.
Doesn't have to be.
You need to go
to the police, Kevin.
You need to tell them that
they have the wrong man.
[ Knock on door ]
Come in.
You know, I've thought about it,
and I thought, "You know what?
I've already spilled my guts
to you."
And -- And since
I'm perfectly at ease
talking to a complete stranger,
which I have no explanation for,
it makes sense that I
would be comfortable
speaking to you here.
So, if you're still
willing to treat me...
I am.
And based on
our previous discussion,
you have some intriguing
issues to work out.
Uh...referring back
to our conversation,
I-I just have to ask,
just to be sure...
When we met
at Charlie's,
did you know that
I was your patient?
♪♪
So, supposedly,
there's a procedure
that could, um
[inhales deeply]
possibly undo
what had been done to me.
Well, forgive me, I-I-I don't
know what happened to you.
Long story.
Heard plenty of
"long stories," brother.
[ Laughs ]
Yeah, not like this,
I can assure you.
You know how, um...
you said you were surprised
to hear that I went AWOL?
Yeah.
Well, that wasn't
the case.
I was abducted.
I knew it.
I knew it. I knew you would
never abandon your post.
That's what happened
to you...
Well, the plan
was to, uh...
put me in
my brother's place to, uh...
transfer his knowledge,
his memories into my head,
and then
he could be eliminated.
Yeah, but he's still
around, so...
someone messed up.
First part worked.
I got his memories,
and, uh, well, I lost my own.
Now, you said that
there was some procedure
that could help
you recover your memories.
Now, why -- why --
why wouldn't you do that?
What -- What could be
holding you back?
♪♪
Maybe Sonny could persuade
Shiloh to leave town?
No, no, no, no, no.
No,
that could backfire.
Shiloh could
tell Kristina.
Kristina -- she could dig in
so much harder.
No way.
All right.
Oh, I hate this.
I hate this
for everyone.
You and Jason just
got back together.
I'd like to wring
Shiloh's enlightened neck.
I've got to pretend
to hang on to his every word.
God.
Yeah.
What if he catches on
that you're playing him?
Well, I've -- I-I-I have
thought about this,
and I've got a few things
going for me.
One: I am
an experienced con.
Two: Shiloh expects women
to fall for him,
including Kristina.
I mean, and
all these other girls,
they're almost like
his groupies,
and he assumes
he can pull me in.
All I have to do
is play along.
Shiloh is naturally warm
and inclusive,
and that can be misunderstood
by some of our more...
vulnerable volunteers.
So, what does Shiloh do
about that?
He handles it.
He handles it?
I-I mean,
like I said,
my friend's vulnerable
and -- and naive.
I just -- I don't --
I don't want her to get hurt,
so, I mean, what d--
how does he handle --
Cop Billy: Jason Morgan?
Yeah. Um...
is there --
is there a problem?
Ran your plates.
Seems you have an arrest record
here in Beechers Corners.
For murder.
Yeah, those --
those charges were dropped.
Yes, I know, but you're on
the wrong side of the law again.
♪♪
Dove Intensive Repair
conditioner proves it can.
We treat one brush
with Dove conditioner...
...and expose both
to heat styling, ...
...to bleaching...
...and even coloring.
The difference is clear.
The brush treated with Dove
is visibly smoother....
...and protected against damage.
♪♪
Dove Intensive Repair
conditioner.
For 100% touchably
beautiful hair.
Since one conditioner
doesn't fit all.
Dove Ultra-Care Conditioners.
♪ They say quit
they say done ♪
♪ They say we're
too grown for fun ♪
♪ They say old,
we say young ♪
♪ We say playful's never done ♪
♪ Don't fight the feeling
just let it flow ♪
♪ Stack it up,
rack it up, let it go ♪
♪ Laughter is calling
pick up the phone ♪
♪ Let's stay playful, Oreo ♪
Hello?
Psych!
♪ If we're still smiling
the future's bueno ♪
♪ I got a secret
the world should know ♪
♪ Let's stay playful, Oreo ♪
♪
Real cheese people are
ham and swiss people.
They're hot and cold.
Big and bold.
But they would never
make a sandwich
with pasteurized
process cheese food.
Sargento slices are 100%
real, natural cheese.
Sargento,
we're real
cheese people.
Stand up to Chronic
Migraine with BOTOX®.
What if you had fewer headaches
and migraines a month?
BOTOX® prevents
headaches and migraines
before they even start.
BOTOX® is for adults
with Chronic Migraine,
15 or more headache
days a month,
each lasting 4 hours or more.
BOTOX® injections take about
15 mins. in your doctor's office
and are covered
by most insurance.
Effects of BOTOX® may spread
hours to weeks after injection
causing serious symptoms.
Alert your doctor right away,
as difficulty swallowing,
speaking, breathing,
eye problems,
or muscle weakness
can be signs of a
life-threatening condition.
Side effects may
include allergic reactions,
neck and injection site pain,
fatigue, and headache.
Don't receive BOTOX® if
there's a skin infection.
Tell your doctor your
medical history, muscle or
nerve conditions,
and medications,
including botulinum toxins,
as these may increase the
risk of serious side effects.
With the BOTOX® Savings Program,
most people with
commercial insurance
pay nothing out of pocket.
Talk to your doctor and visit
BOTOXChronicMigraine.com
to enroll.
It's your weekend to save,
during Pier 1's storewide
Presidents Day Sale.
February 14th through the 18th.
Get up to $100 off
our most loved items.
Get started on
your spring refresh
with big savings this weekend.
In store and at pier1.com.
♪ I'M A BIG KID NOW ♪
♪ WENT FROM BABY BOTTLES TO
DRINKING FROM SIPPY CUPS ♪
♪ WENT FROM WEARING DIAPERS TO
ROCKING THESE FRESH PULL-UPS ♪
♪ WE'RE 50 MILLION STRONG ♪
♪ SO PUT ON YOUR PULL-UPS
AND HELP US SING THIS SONG ♪
You called to make
this appointment at
5:00 this afternoon.
At which time, I was already
sitting down at Charlie's
with my book
and my coffee.
So, no -- I didn't know
that the interesting woman
sitting down next to me --
and who I asked to dinner --
was Alexis Davis,
my soon-to-be patient.
And if I did,
I would never
have asked you to dinner.
I apologize for questioning
your professionalism.
Apology accepted.
But, you know,
if we move forward...
can you trust me?
Now, see, there's a lot
to unpack in that question.
Hmm.
I can try.
Well, why don't we, um,
see how today goes,
and if you choose to,
we can continue?
Okay.
♪♪
You were, uh, prompted
to call me this afternoon,
and I'm just wondering
why it was so urgent
to return to therapy
at this point.
Oh, well, there are
a lot of reasons.
Chief among them
i-is the feeling I had
when I saw my ex-husband
kissing his girlfriend,
his new girlfriend.
And then there was yesterday,
I had this experience
at this organization
called Dawn of Day.
♪♪
So, as I
understand it, uh...
the procedure is a lot like
overwriting a computer program.
Yeah.
My old memories
will be restored --
but all the memories I've made
in the past five years
would essentially be eliminated,
deleted.
You know...
The relationships I've made,
people I've grown to love,
memories of
my daughter, Scout.
From the day she was born
up until now, gone.
Hmm.
I didn't even know
I had a son
until I moved
to Port Charles,
so meeting him,
the memories
we've made together...
I'd lose them.
♪♪
They mean
everything to me.
So...
The short answer
is "no."
I will not be having
the procedure.
That's good.
That's good, man. You got
your priorities straight.
[ Chuckles ]
You know the worst part
of this whole thing
is having
to lie to Danny.
I know, he's just
too young to understand
everything
that's going on,
and I know he's gonna be
missing out
on some major
family time.
Can't you guys meet up
at the Quartermaines?
Well, yeah, I'm --
I'm counting on it.
Monica's been
pretty great about that.
She's the ultimate
hands-off mother-in-law.
Monica?
Yeah.
A-Are you serious?
Oh, my gosh,
when I was married to A.J.,
all she did was meddle.
I mean,
I guess I understand,
because A.J. and I loathed
each other, but...
Anyway, I'm just saying,
you guys have a totally
different relationship
than I had.
You know, it's --
it's really funny.
For two people that
can't stand each other,
you two are a lot alike...
In what universe?
You both have
a love for family.
Well, you're a part
of that club, too, Sam.
I mean, look at
everything you're doing
to protect Kristina.
Yeah, but I also
know what it's like
to have a guy use you
and make you
feel worthless
and tear down
your self-esteem.
And I am not gonna let Shiloh
do that to Kristina.
Officer, I've done
nothing wrong.
I'm just trying to sit here
and have a conversation...
Could there be some
kind of mistake?
No mistake.
Mr. Morgan's vehicle
is parked too close to
a designated handicapped spot.
Th-There was no --
There was no sign.
They're difficult to see,
even in the daylight.
I need you to move it now,
or I'll have it impounded.
It's okay, Billy.
Billy.
Mr. Morgan will move
his car shortly. Okay?
We're just wrapping
things up here.
But thank you
for your diligence.
[ Sighs ]
Sure thing, Harmony.
Okay.
♪♪
I'm sorry.
His bark is worse
than his bite.
Yeah, well, thank you
for smoothing that over.
Yeah.
It's wonderful
how this community
looks out
for each other.
It's really come together
since Dawn of Day launched here.
I hope we can bring
that same sort of fellowship
to Port Charles.
Is there anything else
you'd like to know?
I think
I've heard enough.
I hope I've calmed
your anxieties
on behalf
of your...person.
Do you feel more comfortable
about Dawn of Day now?
I've learned a lot.
Look, I-I-I'm sorry.
Really, I-I-I don't know
what came over me.
It's just...
Look, I don't know
what's worse --
thinking about Kiki,
or -- or -- or
not thinking about her.
I-I'm consumed
with missing her.
I-I can't seem to find
a moment's peace.
So, how did you
get those bruises?
I noticed them
when I came in.
Did you get mugged
or something?
Uh...boxing.
I-I spar sometimes.
With those neurosurgeon hands?
Are you crazy?
No, we, uh --
we wear gloves.
You know, big --
big, padded ones.
Okay, well, pick someone
your own size next time.
[ Chuckles ] Looks like
you were boxing a kangaroo.
No, I just, uh...
I just lost focus,
that's all.
I...
My mind wanders, and, uh,
regret just takes over.
I know the feeling.
What do you
have to regret?
♪♪
It's important
that the police
stop wasting their time
on Franco --
and -- and find
the monster who killed Kiki.
I know you're struggling
with terrible grief,
and I didn't want to add to it
by upsetting you...
You didn't. It's -- It isn't
your fault that I overreacted.
But you ran
right back to Griffin.
[ Chuckles ] What?
Oh, you saw Griffin
comforting me
and you assumed that
I went back to him?
Ava, you ran out on me.
And you're
so beautiful, and...
Come on.
Let's face it --
the man's an Adonis,
and...
Naturally, I just
thought that --
You --
You're insane.
You know that?
And I'd have to be equally
insane to go back to the man
who betrayed me
with my own daughter.
Kevin...
[ Chuckling ] Oh, Kevin.
♪♪
The Russells travel to a
different swim meet every
Saturday.
But now... it's Thursday.
Good thing they discovered Gain
Flings.
The only detergent with
concentrated Gain,
Oxi Boost, and Febreze Odor
Remover.
Mmhmm. Smelling is believing.
And Gain Flings can HIYA Karate
stink too.
Try new improved Gain Flings.
Not having a good breakfast
can make you feel
like your day never started.
Get going with Carnation
Breakfast Essentials®.
It has protein,
plus 21 vitamins
and minerals
including calcium
and vitamin D,
to help your family
be their best.
Carnation Breakfast
Essentials®.
Searching for a way to
help stop your cold sore?
t Only Abreva canly
get rid of it in...
...as little as 2 1/2 days
when used at the first sign.
Abreva starts to
work immediately
to block the virus and
protect healthy cells.
Abreva acts on it.
So you can too.
♪ I'M A BIG KID NOW ♪
♪ WENT FROM BABY BOTTLES TO
DRINKING FROM SIPPY CUPS ♪
♪ WENT FROM WEARING DIAPERS TO
ROCKING THESE FRESH PULL-UPS ♪
♪ WE'RE 50 MILLION STRONG ♪
♪ SO PUT ON YOUR PULL-UPS
AND HELP US SING THIS SONG ♪
Gentle means everything,
so we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients
Added one handed pumps
And beat the
top safety standards
The new JOHNSON'S®
Choose Gentle
I'm a fighter.
Always have been.
When I found out I had
Age-related Macular
Degeneration,
AMD,
I wanted to fight back.
My doctor and I came up
with a plan.
It includes
PreserVision.
Only PreserVision
AREDS 2
has the exact
nutrient formula
recommended by the
National Eye Institute
to help reduce the risk
of progression of moderate
to advanced AMD.
That's why I fight.
Because it's
my vision.
PreserVision.
Also, in a great-tasting
chewable.
(coughs)
Hi Susan!
Honey? I respect that.
But that cough looks
pretty bad...
try this NEW Robitussin Honey.
The real honey you love...
Plus the powerful cough
relief you need.
Mind if I root through
your trash?
New Robitussin Honey.
Because it's never just a cough.
Allergies with sinus
congestion and pressure?
You won't find relief here.
Go to the pharmacy counter
for powerful Claritin-D.
While the leading allergy spray
only relieves 6 symptoms,
Claritin-D relieves 8, including
sinus congestion and pressure.
Claritin-D relieves more.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
[ Sighs ]
I-I came to Port Charles
with zero expectations.
I was gonna blow in,
meet my biological mother,
and blow out.
And then I met Nina,
and Kiki, and Charlotte,
and all these people that
I came to care about.
And I found myself
worrying about you all,
hoping that
you were all okay.
That's good.
[ Chuckles ]
That's --
That's a good thing.
You made --
You made connections.
I just want
to do the right thing,
but I'm not sure how.
There are things that are
[exhales sharply]
hard to fix.
♪♪
You want
to talk about it?
I'm, uh -- I'm open,
wide-open
to distractions, um...
And I-I really
want to help.
Thanks.
♪♪
[ Chuckles ]
Why is it so hot in here?
It's the building.
You can't -- You can't
control the radiator.
Kiki showed me
a few tricks,
but I never really
got the hang of it.
You know, she had
the -- the magic touch...
♪♪
...with everything
she did.
[ Sighs ]
Are you okay?
I really thought
I had lost you.
[ Exhales sharply ]
You know...
it's only been a short time,
Ava, but...
you have my heart.
[ Chuckles ]
You're everything
to me.
I don't think
I'd be able to go on
putting one foot in front
of the other if I --
if I'd lost
the woman I love.
♪♪
You...
You love me?
In an effort to try to
heal this rift between
my daughter and me,
I agreed
to attend a seminar
led by this man
that she respects.
And how was it?
Weird.
Completely uncomfortable,
but I played nicely in order
to appease my daughter,
and in that,
I ended up admitting
that I have this yearning
to have the same feeling
that I had when I was
with my ex.
And as you astutely
put it,
y-you said that
I tend to "frame everything
in -- in the context
of my ex,"
and I-I-I don't want
to do that anymore.
Um...
I'm, uh, fairly certain
that I don't want a relationship
with him again.
However, his type,
that type is the type
that I am, uh, drawn to.
So, you have a type?
Oh, I do.
I do, yes. Um...
Um, Dangerous.
Selfish.
Incapable of intimacy
and honesty, and...
someone who loves power more
than they will ever love me.
Is there a man
in your life
who, uh, set this pattern
up for you?
My father.
You know,
it's a small world,
because he's one of those
exiled Russian aristocrats
that you're so fond
of studying.
Hmm.
Shiloh:
That is a lot of pain that
you're carrying around, man.
And if you ever
just want to reconcile
what happened to you
or -- or just vent...
my seminars have helped ease
a lot of suffering.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Including your own?
Well, they're a result
of my own breakthroughs,
you know?
Hmm.
I've learned to untie
from my troubled past.
And now that I know that it's
no longer burdening you, either,
well, looks like we both
could have a little closure.
Tell you what.
No charge.
[ Chuckles ]
Hell, maybe I should
start my own seminars.
♪♪
Looks like you've given me
my life back yet again.
Thank you.
Okay.
All right.
♪♪
Thanks for coming by, man.
It was good seeing you.
Thanks for having me.
Anytime.
♪♪
I'd invite you
to attend an open house
here or
in Port Charles,
but something tells me
that'll never happen.
You know, I really wish you'd
open your mind and accept help.
You must bear scars
being arrested
for a murder that
you didn't commit.
No. I don't.
Thank you for your time.
♪♪
Okay, I-I know that
you and Jason aren't
candy-hearts-and-flowers
kind of people,
but you should be together
on Valentine's Day.
I have plans
You're going to that event
at Dawn of Day, aren't you?
I've seen the fliers --
"True Love Begins
with Self Love."
[ Laughs ]
Shiloh's expecting me.
Ugh, well, you can
have an emergency.
You know, a tire could blow,
anything.
Oh, God.
No, no, no, no.
That is very tempting.
Don't do that.
I will not be spending
Valentine's Day
with the man
that I love.
I will be at
the Dawn of Day house,
soaking up
all of Shiloh's...
wisdom with an eager smile
on my face.
Because the harder
I sell this...
the faster I can
get Kristina out of there.
(Announcer)
Do you push through migraine?
(Daughter)
Mom, are you OK to play?
(Mom)
Yeah honey, how about we play...
princess and pirates?
(Announcer)
Imagine what you can do with
more migraine-free days.
(Pirate)
Arr!
(Mom)
En garde!
(Announcer)
When you're not fighting
through migraine
imagine the possibilities.
Once-monthly Emgality is used
for the prevention
of migraine in adults.
It's specifically developed to
help give you
more migraine-free days.
With Emgality about 60% of
people had their migraine days
cut in half or more.
Do not use if you are allergic
to Emgality or its ingredients.
Emgality may cause allergic
reactions, such as
itching, rash, hives and
trouble breathing,
which can happen days after use.
Call your doctor or get medical
help right away
if you have symptoms of an
allergic reaction.
The most common side
effects include
injection site reactions.
(Mom)
What should we do tomorrow?
(Announcer)
Ask your doctor about Emgality.
Learn about savings at
Emgality.com
Does removing makeup
feel like this?
Your skin deserves better.
Garnier Micellar Cleansing Water
with micelles that
work like a magnet.
It's a pure way to remove
stubborn makeup
without harsh rubbing.
Cleansing, reinvented.
Micellar Water.
By Garnier,
Naturally!
This time, it's his turn.
You have 4.3 minutes
to yourself.
This calls for a
taste of cheesecake.
Philadelphia Cheesecake Cups.
Rich, creamy cheesecake
with real strawberries.
Find them with the
refrigerated desserts.
At last, one red that works on
everyone.
New Made for All lip color from
Maybelline New York.
Tested on 50 skin tones.
Sensational on all.
New Made for All.
Only from Maybelline New York.
♪
Cats will do anything
for the irresistible taste of
TEMPTATIONS™ treats.
What are you doing?
Oh hey, check this out.
TEMPTATIONS ™.
All
It Takes
Is A Shake™.
(Thunderclap)
If your day doesn't
unfold as predicted.
Unfold this.
New Neutrogena®
Makeup Remover single.
And remove 99% of makeup.
100% rain or shine.
Neutrogena®.
Announcing our Biggest Event
Ever.
More ways to save on brands
you love.
More furniture.
More rugs...
Lamps...
Art.
Come in for huge savings,
right now.
Go finding today. HomeGoods.
You can't put a price on love.
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
>> TECH: At Safelite AutoGlass
we know that when you're
spending time with the grandkids
every minute counts.
And you don't have time
for a cracked windshield.
That's why we
show you exactly
when we'll be there.
Saving you time, so you
can keep saving the world.
>> KIDS: ♪ Safelite repair,
Safelite replace ♪
The day after chemo
shouldn't mean going
back to the doctor
just for a shot.
With Neulasta Onpro
patients get their day back...
to be with family,
or just to sleep in.
Strong chemo can put you at
risk of serious infection.
In a key study Neulasta
reduced the risk of infection
from 17% to 1%,
a 94% decrease.
Neulasta Onpro is designed
to deliver Neulasta
the day after chemo
and is used by most patients
today.
Neulasta is for certain
cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta if you're
allergic to it
or Neupogen (filgrastim).
An incomplete dose could
increase infection risk.
Ruptured spleen,
sometimes fatal as well as
serious lung problems,
allergic reactions,
kidney injuries and capillary
leak syndrome have occurred.
Report abdominal or shoulder
tip pain, trouble breathing
or allergic reactions to
your doctor right away.
In patients with sickle
cell disorders,
serious, sometimes fatal crises
can occur.
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
Ask your doctor about
Neulasta Onpro.
Pay no more than $5 per dose
with copay card.
So, if it's okay with you,
I think maybe we could skip over
the gory details
of my family,
because if we go through
all the twists and turns,
we're gonna be here
all year, right?
So, if I can
just sum it all up by saying
that my father was...
distant, unapproachable,
and a controlling figure
in my life.
He was, um...ruthless,
and powerful,
and I was simultaneously
drawn to him
and repelled by him.
I rarely got
his attention,
and I never earned
his love...
Which would explain
why I've had
a string of
hideous relationships
with ruthless
and unattainable men.
You mentioned earning
your father's love.
Yeah, that's not your job
to earn your father's love.
Parental love is a gift --
no strings attached.
Then you don't know
my family,
because in my family,
love is not a gift.
It's a weakness
to be exploited.
And at what age
did you realize that?
Oh. Well,
I have no idea,
because I've blocked out
most of my childhood.
Did I mention that my stepmother
murdered my mother --
and I witnessed it?
♪♪
Um, you probably have suffered
some, uh, post-traumatic stress.
Have you ever been
diagnosed or treated?
No.
So, uh, where does
your father fit in here?
Well, he was the only one
that would --
could check
my stepmother,
because he was as ruthless
and cruel as she was.
So perhaps you equate cruelty
and ruthlessness to safety.
Only powerful men --
as selfish
and unattainable
as they are --
assure you
your survival.
♪♪
You know, I-I never really
thought about it like that.
Well...
[ Notebook thuds ]
...if we decide
to move forward,
we can help you
lead yourself
to a better understanding
of yourself.
Start guiding you away
from the people
that are not good for you
or to you,
and maybe lead you
to healthier relationships.
I think I'd like that.
So, another appointment?
Yeah.
I was hoping to save those words
for Valentine's Day.
Don't.
Please.
I won't.
♪♪
I love you.
I love you, too.
I love you very much.
♪♪
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to
bring up Kiki again for you...
I really should be
heading out...
Uh, thank you
for stopping by.
If I come back,
I'll bring ice packs.
[ Chuckles ] You're welcome
to stop by anytime.
Just, um...
do me a favor --
work on those regrets.
You're just too young to have
that weighing on you.
So are you.
♪♪
Harmony.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
You sound upbeat.
Well, it is a beautiful night.
And I have just discovered
that a potential threat
isn't so threatening at all.
Well, I thought
you should know...
I just met with
a Jason Morgan.
He was questioning me
about you.
Yeah, yeah, I expected that.
What's the upshot?
I arranged for an assist
from our favorite cop Billy.
Oh, wonderful.
Well, I hope he made Jason
feel less than welcome.
No, Billy did his part.
Jason didn't seem
to be intimidated,
but I doubt he'll be back
in Beechers Corners.
He didn't learn anything
we didn't want him to know.
That's good.
♪♪
Hey!
You just missed Sam.
Or was that intentional?
Uh, one of your --
one of your bartenders
is into Dawn of Day.
What?
Which one?
No idea --
Sonny was talking to him.
Damn it.
I mean,
I can't fire him.
But I also don't want him
here lurking around,
reporting everything
back to Shiloh.
I really wanted this to be
a safe place for you and Sam.
It's okay, Carly. We'll f--
We'll find a safe place.
[ Sighs ]
I can't tell you
how unsettling it is
that this Shiloh guy
was able to make inroads for
a long time and no one noticed.
[ Sighs ]
Do you know that
Dawn of Day was behind
the clothing drive that the kids
were a part of last fall?
Mm-hmm.
Had I known that, I would have
never let Josslyn participate!
Okay, okay,
Josslyn is not vulnerable.
She has a great sense
of herself...
Okay, it's Kristina.
She's the one who's in deep.
Really?
Okay, do you think Sam's gonna
be able to pull her out?
I don't know.
It might --
It might help
if Shiloh's distracted.
You know, feeling a little
pressure from the outside.
What kind of pressure?
I'm not sure.
I took a trip up
to Beechers Corners
to check out
the original Dawn of Day,
and it did give me a good idea
of how it works.
But now...
I got to figure out
how to take it down.