>>> THE PRESIDENT GIVES HIS
SECOND STATE OF THE UNION
ADDRESS WHICH IS A CALL FOR
UNITY, BUT DEMOCRATS HIT BACK
SAYING THE PROBLEM WITH UNITY
IS HIS FAULT.
>>> WAS THE PRESIDENT RIGHT
WHEN HE SAID ICE MADE HUNDREDS
OF ARRESTS?
>> FROM RECORD HEAT YESTERDAY
TO NEEDING A JACKET AND AN
UMBRELLA TODAY.
>>> AND ONE STATE IS GOING TO
EXTREME MEASURES TO CRACK DOWN
ON SMOKING, BUT DON'T WORRY,
YOUR BOAT IS SAFE.
GET UP DC.
[ MUSIC ]
>>> [ APPLAUSE ] GET UP DC, IT
IS 6:00 AND AN ENCOURAGING 46
DEGREES RIGHT NOW.
PRESIDENT TRUMP DELIVERED HIS
SECOND STATE OF THE UNION
ADDRESS LAST NIGHT AND THIS IS
THE FIRST SINCE DEMOCRATS TOOK
CONTROL OF THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES.
WE WILL HAVE MORE ON THAT
THROUGH THE NEXT HOUR, BUT WE
STARTED WITH THE UNION, A
QUESTION.
DO YOU THINK IT WILL HELP UNITE
BOTH PARTIES YES OR NO OR IT
NEVER HAD A CHANCE.
YOU CAN VOTE ON WUSA9.COM/BOAT
OR THE  WUSA9 APP.
I NEED TO ASK YOU, WILL I GET
TO WEAR MY TANK TOP AGAIN
TODAY?
BECAUSE THE  GUN SHOW WAS
SPARSELY ATTENDED YESTERDAY.
>> YOU WILL WANT A JACKET LIKE
THE ONE YOU ARE WEARING RIGHT
NOW.
OUT OF THE DOOR THIS MORNING,
40s AND 30s, 47 IN, CALL IT A
WEATHER FLIP-FLOP BECAUSE WE
HAVE COLDER TEMPERATURES TODAY,
HIGHS ONLY BETWEEN 48 AND 55
DEGREES WITH SHOWERS OUT THERE
AND THE BEST TIME TO SEE THE
SHOWERS ACROSS METRO DC IS
GOING TO BE AROUND 5:00 OR SO
THIS AFTERNOON AND NORTH AND
WEST OF DC, YOU COULD SEE THE
SHOWERS AS EARLY AS 2:00.
2:30 P.M., SHOWERS OVER
MARTINSBURG AND FREDERICK AND
6:00 THIS AFTERNOON HAS SHOWERS
ACROSS METRO DC WITH LIGHT RAIN
FALLING ACROSS THE AREA.
THAT WILL LAST US THROUGH AT
LEAST THE DINNERTIME HOURS.
ONE OF THE REASONS WE ISSUED
THE YELLOW WEATHER ALERT, BUT
WE SEE THE TEMP IS GOING UP AND
DOWN AND BACK TO THE 60s FOR
THURSDAY AND FRIDAY WITH
SHOWERS AND STRONG COLD FRONT,
THAT SENDS US DOWN TO 39 FOR
THE HIGH ON SATURDAY.
>> BACK TO REALITY.
AND WE HAD A CLOSURE ON ROUTE
5, THAT DOWN IN ST. MARY'S, BUT
IT'S IN SOUTHBOUND LANES AND IT
INVOLVES A COMMUTER BUS AND
UTILITY VEHICLES BY THREE NOTCH
ROAD, ALL SOUTHBOUND LANES ARE
CLOSED.
DC 295 HAS FOUR VEHICLES
INVOLVED IN THE CRASH BY SOUTH
CAPITOL STREET.
ABOUT 28 PASSING BY ROUTE 7
SOUTHBOUND HAS AN ACCIDENT AS
WELL.
>>> KEEP VOTING AND WHETHER YOU
THINK THE STATE OF THE UNION
ADDRESS WILL HELP OUR TWO
POLITICAL PARTIES BRIDGE THE
DIVIDE.
MATT GREGORY HAS MORE ON THE
SPEECH.
WHAT WERE THE TAKEAWAYS?
>> Reporter: ONE OF THE BIG
TAKEAWAYS WAS THE PRESIDENT
FIRST CALL FOR UNITY AND USE
THE SPEECH AS A RALLYING CRY
FOR ACCOMPLISHMENTS HE'S
ALREADY DONE AND OTHER ISSUES
HE WOULD LIKE TO SEE HAPPEN.
DEMOCRATS HIT BACK SAYING ANY
LACK OF UNITY IN THE COUNTRY,
ANY DISCORD COMES FROM THE
PRESIDENT, HIMSELF.
HERE ARE THREE THINGS TO KNOW
FROM THE STATE OF THE UNION AND
RESPONSE, PRESIDENT TRUMP
CALLED FOR CONGRESS TO PASS
TIGHTER BORDER SECURITY
MEASURES INCLUDING A CONTINUED
CALL FOR A BORDER WALL BETWEEN
THE U.S. AND MEXICO AND THE
PRESIDENT REVEALED HE WILL HAVE
ANOTHER MEETING WITH NORTH
KOREAN PRESIDENT KIM JONG-UN.
THAT WILL TAKE PLACE FEBRUARY
27 AND 28 IN VIETNAM AND THE
GOAL IS TO GET AN AGREEMENT FOR
DENUCLEARIZATION.
AND GEORGIA DEMOCRAT STACEY
ABRAMS BLAMED THE PRESIDENT FOR
THE DIVISIVENESS IN THE COUNTRY
AND POINTED TO THE 35 DAY
PARTIAL GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN AS
AN EXAMPLE OF HIS REFUSAL TO
COMPROMISE AND HOW THAT HURT
THE COUNTRY.
IT IS IMPORTANT TO NOTE THAT
THE TEMPORARY FUNDING FOR THE
PARTIAL GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN
RUNS OUT ON FEBRUARY 15. SO IF
THE DEMOCRATS AND PRESIDENT
DON'T COME TO SOME SORT OF
AGREEMENT BETWEEN NOW AND THEN,
WE COULD BE HEADING FOR ANOTHER
PARTIAL GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
>> WHILE THE SPEECH WAS GOING
ON, THE VERIFIED TEAM WAS
CHECKING TO SEE WHAT THE
PRESIDENT WAS SAYING AND IF IT
WAS TRUE OR NOT.
>> AS YOU KNOW, THERE'S A LOT
OF FACT CHECKING TO DO WITH
THESE SPEECHES, THE FIRST WE
ARE LOOKING AT IS ABOUT JOBS.
>> AND JUST OVER 2 YEARS SINCE
THE ELECTION, WE'VE TRADED 5.3
MILLION NEW JOBS AND IMPORT OF
THE ADDED 600,000 NEW
MANUFACTURING JOBS.
>> TO GET THE ANSWERS, WENT TO
THE BUREAU OF LABOR STATISTICS
AND ACCORDING TO THE BUREAU,
ONCE THE 2017 INAUGURATION, THE
ECONOMY ADDED 4.9 MILLION NEW
JOBS, NOT 5.3, SO THAT CLAIM IS
FALSE.
TRUMP SAID SINCE THE ELECTION,
IF YOU ADD THE MONTH SINCE
NOVEMBER, THAT ADDS UP TO 5.3
MILLION, BUT BECAUSE THEY
DIDN'T TAKE OFFICE UNTIL THE
NEXT JANUARY, HE GETS CREDIT
FOR THOSE JOBS, WHO GETS CREDIT
IS UP FOR DEBATE.
THE NEXT CLAIM IS ABOUT THE
BORDER.
>> IN THE LAST 2 YEARS, OUR
BRAVE VICE OFFICERS MADE
266,000 ARRESTS OF CRIMINAL
ALIENS, INCLUDING THOSE CHARGED
OR CONVICTED OF NEARLY 100,000
ASSAULTS, 30,000 SEX CRIMES,
AND 4000 KILLINGS.
>> DATA KEPT BY ICE BACKS THESE
NUMBERS UP SO WE CAN VERIFY
THIS IS TRUE, ALTHOUGH THERE IS
IMPORTANT CONTEXT, ABOUT HALF
OF THEM WERE FOR ASSAULT AND
SEX CRIMES AND MURDERING THE
OTHER HALF FOR NONVIOLENT
CRIMES INCLUDING ILLEGAL ENTRY
AND THE NEXT IS ABOUT NORTH
KOREA.
>> OUR HOSTAGES HAVE COME HOME.
NUCLEAR TESTING HAS STOPPED.
AND THERE HAS NOT BEEN A
MISSILE LAUNCH IN MORE THAN 15
MONTHS.
>> A LITTLE BACK STORY, THREE
AMERICANS WERE DETAINED AND
RETURNED IN MAY 2018.
TO ANSWER THE NUCLEAR QUESTION,
WE TURN TO NORTH KOREAN EXPERT
THAT SAYS EVEN THOUGH THE
COUNTRY COULD DO SCIENTIFIC
RESEARCH AND COMPUTER
SIMULATION ON WEAPONS OF MASS
DESTRUCTION, THEY STOPPED
FIRING MISSILES OVER THE KOREAN
PENINSULA.
WE CAN VERIFY THAT THIS IS TRUE
AND AS YOU MENTIONED BEFORE, WE
HAVE A LIVE BLOG RUNNING TO
FACT CHECK TRUMP AND STACEY
ABRAMS AND THEY CHECKED ON WAY
MORE.
I KNOW YOU HAVE THE FINAL
THOUGHT COMING UP ON THE STATE
OF THE UNION COMING UP LATER AS
WELL.
MAKE A BUNCH OF NOTABLE
OMISSIONS, BUT IT IS A CRAZY
STATE OF AFFAIRS WHERE WE NEED
THIS LEVEL OF FACT CHECKING.
>> ESPECIALLY WHEN THEY GO
LONG, THIS WAS THE THIRD
LONGEST EVER, THE LONGEST SINCE
CLINTON.
82 MINUTES, THAT'S A LOT TO
CRAM IN.
>> IF YOU HAVE SOMETHING YOU
WANT VERIFIED, LET OUR
RESEARCHERS GET TO THE BOTTOM
OF IT.
SEND US THE EMAIL AT VERIFY AT
WUSA9.COM.
MOST OF YOU THINK THE SPEECH
NEVER HAD A CHANCE AND THANK
YOU FOR VOTING  NEVER HAD A
CHANCE, YOU COULD HAVE EASILY
VOTED NO, BUT NEVER HAD A
CHANCE ACKNOWLEDGES YOU CAME IN
WITH PRE-EXISTING FEELINGS.
KEEP VOTING ALL MORNING LONG.
THAT'S CHECK THE MOMENTS THAT
CAUGHT SOCIAL MEDIA ATTENTION.
>> LOTS OF PEOPLE TALKING ABOUT
IT.
THERE WAS A STRIKING VISUAL IN
ANY PARTS OF THE CROWD DURING
THE STATE OF THE UNION.
DOZENS OF DEMOCRATIC WOMEN OF
CONGRESS DRESSED IN ALL WHITE
AS A TRIBUTE TO SUFFRAGETTES.
MANY OF THEM ARE FIRST-TIME
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS AND
CURRENTLY A RECORD-BREAKING 102
WOMEN SERVING IN THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES.
THIS YEAR MARKS 100 YEARS SINCE
CONGRESS PASSED AN AMENDMENT
GIVING WOMEN THE RIGHT TO VOTE
AND ONE MOMENT THAT SURPRISED
PEOPLE LAST NIGHT, IT WAS THIS,
RIGHT HERE ASTRONAUT BUZZ
ALDRIN MADE A SURPRISE
APPEARANCE.
THE 89-YEAR-OLD IS ONE OF THE
FIRST TWO PEOPLE TO STEP ON THE
MOON.
HE USED HIS APPEARANCE TO
PROMISE TO RETURN AMERICAN
ASTRONAUTS TO THE BASE.
[ MUSIC ] ♪ HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO
YOU.
CANNOT BACK
>> BOTH PARTIES UNIFY TO SING
HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO AN AMAZING
MAN.
HE IS A SURVIVOR OF THE
HOLOCAUST AND WAS INSIDE THE
TREE OF LIFE SYNAGOGUE IN
PITTSBURGH DURING A MASS
SHOOTING LAST YEAR.
THEY THANKED EVERYONE IN THE
CROWD FOR THE SONG, AND
BREAKING NEWS FROM OVERNIGHT,
FIRE FORCES FOR PEOPLE OUT OF
THEIR HOME IN SOUTHEAST DC.
FIREFIGHTERS WERE CALLED TO A
ROW HOME ON E STREET AROUND
11:00 LAST NIGHT.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS, YOU CAN
SEE HOW INTENSE THE BIG FLAMES
WERE.
WHEN CREWS ARRIVED, FLAMES SHOT
OUT OF A SECOND STORY WINDOW.
WE ARE TOLD THE FIRE WAS
ISOLATED TO JUST ONE ROOM AND
CREWS QUICKLY GOT THINGS UNDER
CONTROL.
INVESTIGATION INTO THE CAUSE IS
UNDERWAY.
WE ARE TOLD THAT THE POOR
PEOPLE DISPLACED WERE ABLE TO
FIND OTHER PLACES TO STAY.
AND HAVE YOU EVER SENT A
MESSAGE AND THEN IMMEDIATELY
REGRETTED IT.
IT HAPPENS TO ALL OF US AT SOME
POINT.
FACEBOOK IS ROLLING OUT AN
UNSEND MESSAGE FEATURE TO ITS
MESSENGER APP FOR IOS AND
ANDROID TO DELETE A MESSAGE
FROM A SINGLE OR GROUP CHAT.
YOU JUST HAVE TO TAP ON THE
MESSAGE YOU WANT TO REMOVE AND
PRESS DELETE AND CHOOSE THE
OPTION LABELED DELETE FOR
EVERYONE.
IT GIVES YOU 10 MINUTES TO
RETHINK WHAT YOU JUST SENT.
BUT UNSEND DOESN'T MEAN UNSEEN,
IF YOUR FRIEND IS AT WORK
LOGGING INTO FACEBOOK AND YOU
SEND THEM A PICTURE OR MESSAGE,
IT ALREADY POPS UP IN THE
WINDOW, SO IT IS SEEN, SO YOU
CANNOT THEN DELETE IT.
>> THAT IS MESSED UP ESPECIALLY
VF NOTIFICATIONS ON, SO IT'S AT
THE NOTIFICATION EMAIL EVEN IF
YOU UNSEND IT.
THIS IS INSPIRING TO ALL OF THE
GUYS OUT THERE THAT WERE
FEELING SHY ABOUT JUMPING INTO
DM'S BECAUSE THEY COULD GET
SCREEN SHOT IT, THAT IS A
HORRIBLE REALITY FOR ME, BUT
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
THAT ANYMORE.
ALL OF THESE YOUNG PLAYERS LIKE
JAKE AND GEO, EVERYONE WANTS TO
HOP INTO DM'S, PLAY ON.
>> ADD TO THE DM'S.
>> MY APOLOGY EVERYONE OUT
THERE, YOU ARE ABOUT TO HAVE A
LOT OF MAIL WHEN YOU GET BACK.
WHAT IS ONE THING WE NEED TO
KNOW ABOUT THE FORECAST.
>> THE ONE THING YOU NEED TO
KNOW IS THAT IT IS COOLER TODAY
WITH A CHANCE FOR SHOWERS.
>> WE ALSO HAD PROBLEMS ON I-95
IN MARYLAND HEADING SOUTHBOUND
PASSING BY ROUTE 212, A LIVE
TRAFFIC LANE CAMERA, A TRACTOR-
TRAILER CAUGHT ON CAMERA, THAT
IS OVER ON THE SHOULDER.
IT IS 6:10, IT IS TIME FOR
ANOTHER NEWS WE LOOK AT THE NEW
STORIES THAT MAY NOT BE ON YOUR
RADAR, BUT THEY SHOULD BE.
A BILL IN HAWAII PROPOSES
RAISING THE LEGAL SMOKING AGE
TO 100 YEARS OLD.
IT SUGGESTS THAT SMOKING AGE
SHOULD GO UP TO 30 IN 2020 AND
40 AND 2021, 50 IN 2022 AND 60
IN 2023 AND FINALLY IN, AS THE
70-YEAR-OLDS THINK THE TIME IS
COME, PEOPLE NEED TO BE 100
YEARS OLD TO BUY CIGARETTES.
FAKE ID PRODUCTION IN HAWAII IS
ABOUT TO GET REAL CRAZY.
>>> AND OTHER NEWS, HOWARD
SCHULTZ TOOK PERSONAL OFFENSE
TO BEING DESCRIBED AS A
BILLIONAIRE IN A RECENT
INTERVIEW.
HE SAID PEOPLE SHOULD USE
PEOPLE OF WEALTH OR PEOPLE OF
MEANS TO DESCRIBE HIS CLASS.
HIS CLASS ACCOUNTS FOR 1% OF
THE WORLD'S POPULATION.
IN RESPONSE, THE OTHER 99% OF
US KNOWN AS THE PEOPLE WITH NO
WEALTH WOULD ALSO LIKE A NEW
DESCRIPTION INSTEAD OF BROKE,
WE WOULD LIKE TO BE ADDRESSED
AS BILLIONAIRES.
>>> A JOGGER IN COLORADO
SUFFOCATED AN 80 POUND MOUNTAIN
LION WITH HIS BARE HANDS AFTER
HE WAS ATTACKED ON THE TRAIL.
THE MAN WAS RUNNING AND HEARD
SOMETHING BEHIND HIM AND WHEN
HE TURNED AROUND, HE SAW A
MOUNTAIN LION.
I'M HERE TO MAKE A CONFESSION.
I WAS THAT JOGGER.
THESE ARE THE HANDS OF A MAN
THAT CAN OPEN A PICKLE JAR AND
PROTECT HIMSELF FROM THEM
OUTLINE OR ANY BIG CAT.
I DON'T KNOW MY OWN STRENGTH.
AND IF HE DOESN'T WANT TO COME
FORWARD, I WILL TAKE ALL OF THE
GLORY, IF YOU CAN TAKE THEM
OUTLINE, LET US KNOW WHAT THE
HASHTAG, GET UP DC.
IT IS 6:12, 46 DEGREES AND
COMING UP, REST IN RESIDENCE,
IF YOU THOUGHT YOU HEARD TRAINS
THIS MORNING, YOU WERE NOT
HALLUCINATING.
WE GIVE YOU THE DETAILS IN JUST
A MOMENT.
>> IT'S BEEN FIVE DAYS SINCE A
PHOTO POPPED UP OF THE YEARBOOK
FROM RALPH NORTHAM, CLASSMATES
SAID THAT WAS NOT HIM.
>>> ENDED HIS NATIONAL GIRLS
AND WOMEN IN SPORTS DAY, WE
HAVE ONE OF THE MOST FIT
AUDIENCES YOU HAVE EVER SEEN
THIS ONE WE ARE JOINED BY
MEMBERS OF THE SWIM TEAM FOR
CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY AND THE
DIVE TEAM.
NEXT, WE'LL MEET ONE SWIMMER
WHO IS NOT ONLY SETTING RECORDS
IN THE POOL BUT ALSO BREAKING
GROUND ON
JARDIANCE asked:
When it comes to managing
your type 2 diabetes,
what matters to you?
Let's see.
Most of you say lower A1C.
But only a few of you
are thinking about your heart.
Fact is, even though
it helps to manage A1C,
type 2 diabetes still
increases your risk
of a fatal heart
attack or stroke.
JARDIANCE is the first
type 2 diabetes pill
with a lifesaving
cardiovascular benefit
for adults who have type 2
diabetes and heart disease,
JARDIANCE significantly
reduces the risk of dying
from a cardiovascular event
and lowers A1C,
with diet and exercise.
Let's give it another try.
JARDIANCE can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration.
This may cause you
to feel dizzy, faint,
or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis
is a serious side effect
that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting, stomach pain,
tiredness,
and trouble breathing.
A rare but life-threatening
bacterial infection
in the skin of the genital
area could also occur.
Stop taking JARDIANCE
and call your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of this bacterial infection,
ketoacidosis
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic
reaction include rash,
swelling, and difficulty
breathing or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects are
sudden kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about
all the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
Isn't it time to rethink your
type 2 diabetes medication?
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE
and get to the heart
of what matters.
>>> TODAY IS NATIONAL GIRLS AND
WOMEN IN SPORTS DAY, SO WE
INVITED THE SWIMMING TEAM FROM
CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY TO JOIN US
AND WE ASKED THEM TO NOMINATE
ONE TEAMMATE WHO REALLY
INSPIRED THEM.
>> Reporter: SWIMMING IS ALL
ABOUT REST.
AND EMILY MUSSINA GETS A LOT OF
IT.
THE CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY STUDENT
SPENDS A LOT OF TIME INSIDE
THIS POOL AND SHE WILL ADMIT,
SPORTS ARE KIND OF HER LIFE.
>> I LIKE SPORTS, THAT'S HIGH
UP ON MY LIST.
>> Reporter: AND SHE IS REALLY
GOOD, ONE OF THE BEST ON THE
TEAM, EARNING HER A SPOT ON THE
HANGING BANNER FOR THE FASTEST
200 YARD PLY IN SCHOOL HISTORY.
IT'S NOT JUST SWIMMING, SHE WAS
DOING PLAY-BY-PLAY FOR THE
BASEBALL TEAM, A DREAM OF HERS
SINCE SHE WAS A LITTLE GIRL,
SHE CAN REMEMBER THE EXACT
MOMENT WHEN THE DREAM WAS BORN.
>> 10 YEARS OLD RIDING IN THE
BACKSEAT OF OUR CAR ON A TWO-
HOUR DRIVE TO THE BEACH AND MY
PARENTS ARE YOU, MY PARENTS ARE
LISTENING TO THE YANKEES GAME.
>> SHE HEARD THE BOYS.
>> IT WAS AN AHA MOMENT FOR ME.
I WAS YOUNG, HEARING SOMEONE
ELSE DOING THAT AND KNOWING,
OKAY, THIS COULD BE A REALITY
FOR ME.
>> SINCE THEN, SHE HAS HAD THE
PEDAL TO THE METAL SWIMMING SIX
DAYS A WEEK AND FINDING TIME TO
WORK FOR THE ATHLETIC
DEPARTMENT.
WHEN SHE GRADUATES, SHE WILL
START WORKING FOR THE LYNCHBURG
HILL CAPS IN CENTRAL VIRGINIA
AND SHE KNOWS THAT BASEBALL IS
STILL A MALE DOMINATED
INDUSTRY, BUT THAT WILL NOT
STOP HER.
>> WOMEN CAN DO ANYTHING THEY
WANT, THEY CAN COMPETE ON THE
SAME LEVEL AS MEN, AND THEY
SHOULD AND THEY SHOULD KNOW
THAT THEY ARE WORTH IT AND THEY
SHOULD KNOW THEIR VALUE.
WHY NOT US?
>> I WANT TO SAY THANK YOU TO
EMILY AND THE REST OF HER TEAM
FOR SHOWING UP SO EARLY IN THE
MORNING, YOU ARE IN COLLEGE AND
YOU ARE PROBABLY UP FROM LAST
NIGHT.
AND A SPECIAL SHOUT OUT TO THE
DIVE TEAM, I FORGOT ABOUT THE
THREE OF YOU ON THE DIVE TEAM,
OR IS IT ONLY ONE OF YOU NOW?
>> YOU ARE DIVING FOR
EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU FOR THAT, WE CAUGHT
UP WITH HER COACH TO TALK ABOUT
HER AND YOU CAN FIND THE
INTERVIEW ON OUR WEBSITE,
WUSA9.COM.
>>> DO YOUR THING.
>> I APPRECIATE THE WARM
INTRODUCTION, HERE ARE THREE
THINGS YOU NEED TO KNOW ABOUT
THE FORECAST, WE'VE GOT SHOWERS
TODAY AFTER 2:00 AND MORE RAIN
ON THURSDAY AND FRIDAY AND
COLDER THIS WEEKEND, NEXT WEEK
TRENT, WINTER IS ON ITS WAY
BACK WITH RAIN AND SNOW CHANCES
IN THE FORECAST, ESPECIALLY
MONDAY AND TUESDAY AND
WEDNESDAY.
HE IS WHAT'S HAPPENING RIGHT
NOW, WE HAVE A FRONT THAT IS
LINGERING ACROSS THE AREA.
AS LONG AS IT LINGERS, WE HAVE
CLOUDS OUT THERE AND SHOWERS
AND THAT'S ONE OF THE MAIN
REASONS WE SEE RAIN TODAY.
HIGH TEMPERATURES 40 TO 55
DEGREES, A SHARP DIFFERENCE
FROM YESTERDAY WHERE WE TOPPED
OUT AT 74 DEGREES FOR RECORD
WARM TEMPERATURES.
WHAT A DIFFERENCE A DAY MAKES.
46 BY 10 AM AND 47 BY NOON AND
RIGHT AROUND 48 BY 2:00 THIS
AFTERNOON.
FUTURECAST, YOU NOTICED THE
TEMPERATURES GETTING INTO THE
50s BY THE AFTERNOON AND BY
2:30, THERE IS RAIN OVER
OAKLAND AND CUMBERLAND AND EVEN
TOWARDS MARTINSBURG AND
WINCHESTER.
I 6:00, LIGHT TO MODERATE RAIN
MAKES ITS WAY INTO METRO DC AND
THIS IS ONE OF THE REASONS SOME
OF THE TIMING OF WHY POPPER
MADE THE CALL TO GIVE IT A
YELLOW WEATHER EARLIER TODAY.
8:00 TONIGHT, THERE STILL SOME
RAIN OUT THERE, BREAK LATE
TONIGHT AND THEN TOMORROW
MORNING WE LOOK AT SOME SHOWERS
AND ONCE AGAIN WITH A BREAK IN
THE AFTERNOON AND WARMER
TEMPERATURES REARING UP ONCE
AGAIN.
A STRONG COLD FRONT IS HEADING
AWAY ON FRIDAY.
LOOK AT THE TEMPERATURES AHEAD
OF THE FRONT, 60s AHEAD OF THE
FRONT ON FRIDAY AND THE COLD
AIR COMES SOARING IN AND WE
FIND TEMPERATURES GETTING DOWN
TO THE 30s AND 40s OVER THE
WEEKEND.
WE'VE GOT SOME QUESTIONS ON
SOCIAL MEDIA, JACKSON AND
ROBBIE WANT TO KNOW ABOUT SNOW
HEADING OUR WAY NEXT WEEK.
HERE IT IS, WINTER IS COMING
BACK WITH A RAIN AND SNOW MIXED
POSSIBLE MONDAY MORNING AT THE
LATEST TREND IN THE MODELS HAVE
BEEN TO KEEP THE RAIN AROUND DC
AND KEEP THE RAIN AND SNOW LIED
FURTHER UP TO THE NORTH.
THERE IS STILL TIME TO SORT
THIS OUT, BUT ON TUESDAY, WE
HAVE A CHANCE TO GET A WINTRY
MIX AROUND HERE WITH RAIN AND
SNOW AT PLAY BY LATE TUESDAY
MORNING.
WE ARE WATCHING ALL OF THIS FOR
YOU IN TERMS OF WINTER COMING
BACK.
50s TODAY, 64 ON FRIDAY WITH
FALLING TEMPERATURES AND 39 ON
SATURDAY AND 41 BY SUNDAY.
WE'VE HAD SOME PRETTY SERIOUS
CRASHES OUT THERE THIS MORNING,
ONE ON THE I-95, A TRACTOR-
TRAILER CAUGHT ON FIRE AS HE
TRIED HAD SOUTHBOUND IN
MARYLAND PASSING BY REP TO 12.
THE FIRE IS OUT AND TRAFFIC IS
NOT REALLY JAMMED AS YOU TRY TO
PASS BY THIS BECAUSE THE TRUCK
IS OVER ON THE SHOULDER NOW.
>> WE HAVE AN ACCIDENT WITHOUT
MANY BACKUPS ON ROUTE 28
SOUTHBOUND PAST ROUTE 7. FOR
VEHICLES INVOLVED IN THE CRASH
IN SOUTH BEND BY EAST CAPITOL
STREET, THAT'S BEEN PUSHED OVER
TO THE LEFT SHOULDER AND ON
ROUTE 5, A SERIOUS CRASH IN ST.
MARY'S HEADING SOUTH BEND BY
THREE NOTCH ROAD, ALL OF THE
SOUTHBOUND LANES ARE SLOW.
SO THIS IS A PICTURE FROM THE
SCENE FROM MECHANICSVILLE
VOLUNTEER FIRE DEPARTMENT.
YOU CAN SEE THE COMMUTER BUS
AND NO ONE WAS ON IT, BUT IT
WAS INVOLVED WITH A UTILITY
TRUCK, SOMEONE WAS MEDEVAC.
AND WE ARE SEEING DELAYS ON
ROUTE 5.
>> A NUMBER OF ACCIDENTS, WE
CERTAINLY HOPE EVERYONE EMERGES
Ways to lose
stubborn belly fat:
Metal Vibration Therapy.
( ♪♪ )
(Glass breaking)
(Gasp)
Not cool.
Freezing away fat cells
with CoolSculpting?
Now that's cool!
CoolSculpting safely
freezes and removes fat cells
with little or no downtime
and no surgery.
Results and patient
experience may vary.
Some common side
effects include
temporary numbness,
discomfort, and swelling.
Ask your doctor
if CoolSculpting
is right for you and visit
CoolSculpting.com today
for your chance
to win a free treatment.
(Music blaring)
>>> WELCOME BACK EVERYBODY TO
GET UP DC, IT IS 6:24, HERE ARE
THE THREE THINGS TO KNOW BEFORE
HEADING OUT THIS MORNING,
PEOPLE CONCERNED ABOUT NATURAL
GAS LEAKS IN DC CAN SHARE
EXPERIENCES WITH THE PUBLIC
SERVICE COMMISSION.
THE PSC IS HOLDING THE REGULAR
MEETING AT 2:00 AND AFTER THE
MEETING, COMMUNITY MEMBERS ARE
INVITED TO ASK WASHINGTON GAS
OFFICIALS ABOUT SAFETY AND
PROCEDURES AND PRACTICES AND
MANY MORE THINGS.
PEOPLE FROM RESTON TO JUST
SOUTH OR WEST OF DULLES AIRPORT
MAY HAVE HEARD METRO TRAINS
RUNNING THIS MORNING ON PHASE 2
OF THE SILVER LINE.
EVEN THOUGH IT IS NOT OPEN YET,
METRO SAYS THE TRAINS RAN
BETWEEN 1:00 BEFORE A.M.
TO HELP REMOVE THE RUST FROM
THE THIRD RAIL.
IT CAN BUILD UP SINCE THE LINE
IS NOT IN USE.
THE REAL WORK IS NEEDED SO
METRO CAN START BREAKING TESTS
ON PHASE 2 WHICH IS SET TO OPEN
NEXT YEAR.
AND TODAY IN PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY, THE DEPARTMENT OF
PUBLIC WORKS CREWS CAN START
REPAIRING PESKY POTHOLES THAT
OPENED UP SINCE THE RECENT
SNOWSTORM AND THE COLD SNAP.
YOU CAN REPORT POTHOLES BY
CALLING 31 A. DRIVERS ARE ASKED
TO SLOW DOWN AND GIVE CREWS 20
OF WORK SPACE.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU, BUT MY
CAR IS GETTING PUMMELED BY
THESE POTHOLES.
I HAVE TO GET ALIGNMENT AND
SUSPENSION WORK.
>> THEY NEED TO REPLACE THE
ENTIRE MASSACHUSETTS AVENUE.
JUST THROW THE WHOLE THING AWAY
AND START OVER.
WE NEED A NEW ONE.
>>> IT IS TIME FOR GET AT
REESE, WE FEATURE A COMMENT
THAT GETS IN EVERY DAY.
TODAY COMES ON MY FINAL
THOUGHTS ABOUT RALPH NORTHAM
AFTER A MEDICINE, A MEDICAL
SCHOOL YEARBOOK WAS REVEALED.
THE BACKLASH SEEMED SPORADIC.
TED DANSON WORE BLACK FACE IN
PUBLIC WHILE DATING WHOOPI
GOLDBERG, SHOULDN'T AVERAGE BE
HELD EQUALLY?
I AGREE THIS IS BEEN
UNACCEPTABLE AND INSINCERE,
THANK YOU FOR YOUR COMMENT, BUT
WHAT DOES TED DANSON HAVE TO DO
WITH THIS?
HE IS NOT THE GOVERNOR OF A
STATE, AND HE WAS IN A
POSITION, WHERE HE HAD TO TREAT
AFRICAN-AMERICAN TREATMENTS,
AND HE DID TAKE HEAT, IT WAS
BAD THEN AND IT IS BAD NOW.
IT HAS AND NEVER WILL BE
ACCEPTABLE BUT LET'S NOT PLAY A
BLAME GAME ESPECIALLY WITH TED
DANSON, BLACKFACE IS AND ALWAYS
WILL BE WRONG WHETHER TO 1943
OR 1993 OR 2023.
KEEP SENDING COMMENTS TO ME AT
REESE WATERS ON FACEBOOK AND
TWITTER OR EMAIL R WATERS AT
WUSA9.COM.
YOU CAN ALWAYS USE THE HASHTAG
GET UP DC.
>> IT IS 6:27, 46 DEGREES IN
COMING UP, THE DEMOCRATIC
RESPONSE TO THE STATE OF THE
UNION CALLED FOR TEAMWORK WITH
When was the last time
you felt...
Free.
It's time to uncover
that feeling again.
With the compassion and
strength of a name...
Most accepted by top doctors
and specialists.
And the power of a card...
that opens doors in
all fifty states.
Giving you the freedom to love
to dream to dance
Like no one is watching.
CareFirst
Blue Cross Blue Shield.
Live fearless.
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
CareFirst
Blue Cross Blue Shield.
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>>> NINE FORMER CLASSMATES HAVE
COME FORWARD TO DEFEND GOVERNOR
RALPH NORTHAM SAYING HE WAS NOT
IN THE PHOTO IN THE YEARBOOK
THAT CAME FORWARD JUST YEARS
AGO, JUST DAYS AGO.
>>> THE STATE OF THE UNION
ADDRESS TOUCHED ON TOPICS
INCLUDING NORTH KOREA.
WE HAVE MORE COMING UP.
>>> MUCH COOLER TODAY AFTER THE
TASTE OF SPRING AND SUMMER
YESTERDAY.
>> DC IS A CITY OF BANDWAGON
FANS?
WE FIND OUT IN OUR MOST DC
THING.
GET UP DC.
[ MUSIC ]
>>> GET UP DC, IT IS 46 DEGREES
OUTSIDE.
I AM YOUR HOST, REESE WATERS.
VIRGINIA GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM
STILL HAS HIS JOB TODAY DESPITE
RACIST PHOTOS FROM HIS MEDICAL
SCHOOL YEARBOOK.
ARE YOU ALL SURPRISED HE IS IN
OFFICE?
TWEET US AND LET US KNOW AND
USE THE HASHTAG GET UP DC.
I REALLY WANT TO HEAR WHAT YOU
GUYS THINK.
I WILL HAVE THE LATEST ON WHAT
YOU THINK IF HE DID STEP DOWN,
WILL IT RAIN ON MORE THAN
VIRGINIA TODAY?
>> WE HAVE RAIN CHANCES
AREAWIDE, WE DON'T SEE MUCH OF
THAT RIGHT NOW.
CLOUDY AND 47 AS YOU STEP
OUTSIDE AND BIG CHANGES BETWEEN
TODAY AND YESTERDAY.
SHOWERS WILL PUSH IN AT 230 IN
THE AFTERNOON AND WE COULD SEE
THEM AROUND ROMNEY AND
CUMBERLAND AND IN METRO DC, WE
HAVE THE RAIN FALLING WHICH IS
ONE OF THE REASONS WE HAVE
ISSUED THE YELLOW WEATHER
ALERT.
LIGHT RAIN PUSHING IN DURING
THE EVENING RUSH AND DINNER
HOURS HAS RAIN.
IN TERMS OF HIGH TEMPERATURES,
TODAY IS COOLER THAN YESTERDAY
WITH A RECORD HIGH OF 74 AND
TODAY IS 48 TO 55 DEGREES WITH
SHOWERS AND QUITE CLOUDY.
SPEAKING OF RECORD TEMPERATURES,
BY JANUARY 31, WE HAD A LOW OF
10 DEGREES.
GUESS TODAY WAS 74 AND A 64
DEGREE DIFFERENCE IN A MATTER
OF DAYS.
>> I WILL TAKE THE ONE ON THE
RIGHT.
WE HAVE A NUMBER OF ACCIDENTS,
ROUTE 5 IS STILL CLOSED HEADING
SOUTHBOUND IN ST. MARY'S BY
THREE NOTCH ROAD AND SOUTHBOUND
LANES ARE CLOSED.
WE'VE HAD A MEDEVAC SITUATION,
PRETTY SERIOUS CRASH WITH THE
COMMUTER BUS INVOLVED.
IN FREDERICK, NORTH AND
SOUTHBOUND LANES HAVE BEEN
CLOSED AND WE'VE HAD AN
ACCIDENT BY MOUNDSVILLE ROAD
AND IF YOU ARE IN NORTHEAST,
NEW YORK AVENUE INBOUND HAS
REPORTS OF A CRASH IF YOU TRIED
TO PASS BY BLADEN'S BILL ROAD.
>> IT HAS BEEN FIVE DAYS SINCE
WE LEARNED ABOUT THE RACIST
PHOTOS POSSIBLY CONNECTED TO
VIRGINIA GOVERNOR RALPH
NORTHAM.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN HIM SINCE THE
WILD PRESS CONFERENCE OVER THE
WEEKEND, BUT HE IS STILL
GETTING WORK DONE.
>> WHERE IS HE GETTING SUPPORT
FROM NOW?
>> BASICALLY NINE FORMER
CLASSMATES OF HIS HAVE COME
FORWARD TO DEFEND THE GOVERNOR.
THEY WERE ALL CLASSMATES AT THE
EASTERN VIRGINIA MEDICAL
FACILITY., MEDICAL SCHOOL.
LET'S START RIGHT THERE AND
LOOK AT WHAT THEY WROTE.
>> HERE IS THE STATEMENT, WE
FULLY BELIEVE GOVERNOR RALPH
NORTHAM IS NEITHER OF THE
INDIVIDUALS IN THOSE REPUGNANT
COSTUMES.
WE ATTENDED CLASSES WITH THE
GOVERNOR AND SOCIALIZED WITH
HIM AND WE KNEW HIM VERY WELL,
BUT THINGS REMAIN PRETTY ROCKY
FOR THE EMBATTLED GOVERNOR. HE
HAS BEEN HELD UP IN THE
EXECUTIVE MANSION AND HIS
CALENDAR NOT UPDATED FOR DAYS,
MANY PUBLIC EVENTS HAVE BEEN
CANCELED, BUT BEHIND CLOSED
DOORS COME HE'S TRYING TO
GOVERN.
HE SIGNED OFF ON THE
LEGISLATION TO GIVE AMAZON
MILLIONS IN INCENTIVES AND
YESTERDAY, HE SENT OUT A
STATEMENT SENDING CONDOLENCES
TO THE FAMILY OF A STATE
TROOPER KILLED IN THE LINE OF
DUTY.
THE NEW YORK TIMES IS REPORTING
THAT HE PLANS TO HIRE A PRIVATE
INVESTIGATOR TO LOOK INTO THE
PICTURE AND FIND OUT HOW IT GOT
IN THE YEARBOOK.
MANY LAWMAKERS FROM BOTH
PARTIES, EVEN MANY WHO ARE
TRADITIONAL ALLIES ARE CALLING
FOR HIS RESIGNATION.
>> I CAN'T TELL YOU WHY HE
DIDN'T RESIGN, BUT
>> WE CALL FOR THE RESIGNATION,
THAT'S WHAT THE GOVERNOR DOES.
>> ADDING TO THE CRISIS, SEXUAL
ASSAULT ALLEGATIONS DATING BACK
TO 2004 AGAINST JUSTIN FAIRFAX,
THE LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR WHO
WOULD TAKE OVER IN A NORTHAM
RESIGNATION OFFERED A STRONG
DENIAL.
>> THE ALLEGATION THE VAPORIZER
YEAR AND ONLY RESURFACED ON THE
EVE OF THE ELEVATION GIVEN THE
CURRENT SITUATION, SO IT IS ALL
COMPLETELY POLITICAL AND A
COMPLETE SMEAR.
>> WE ARE LEARNING THAT THE
ACCUSER OF JUSTIN FAIRFAX HAS
HIRED A LAWYER, AND
INTERESTINGLY ENOUGH, IT'S THE
SAME LEGAL TEAM THAT
REPRESENTED CHRISTINE BLASEY
FORD DURING THE NOMINATION OF
RHETT CAVANAUGH.
AS FOR WHETHER HE WILL RESIGN,
AT THIS POINT, THAT IS STILL
ANYONE GAS.
>> AS WE WERE DISCUSSING, IT
WAS INTERESTING WORDING THAT WE
DON'T BELIEVE IT IS HIM HIM AND
NOT THAT WE KNOW THAT IT WASN'T
HIM.
NOT THAT WE HAVE ANY NEW
INFORMATION, WE JUST FEEL LIKE
HE'S NOT THE KIND OF PERSON
THAT WOULD DO SOMETHING LIKE
THAT.
>> INDICATING THAT THEY DON'T
ACTUALLY KNOW, BUT THEY DON'T
THINK HE WOULD BE CAPABLE OF
DOING SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> WE ALL THOUGHT THAT, THAT'S
HOW HE GOT ELECTED.
>> SO WHAT HAPPENS NEXT?
IF HE RESIGNS AND JUSTIN
FAIRFAX TAKES OVER, IF FAIRFAX
STEPS DOWN, WHO TAKES OVER FOR
HIM?
HERE IS SOME CLARITY ABOUT WHAT
THE VIRGINIA LAW SAYS ABOUT WHO
STEPS UP WHEN LEADERS STEP
DOWN.
LET'S ABLE TO GOVERNOR AND
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR STEP DOWN,
WHO TAKES OVER?
WE WENT TO THE VIRGINIA
CONSTITUTION FOR THE ANSWER,
AND ACCORDING TO THE
CONSTITUTION, THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL WOULD BECOME THE ACTING
GOVERNOR.
THAT MAN IS MARK HERRING.
HE IS AN ELIGIBLE HOUSE OF, THE
SPEAKER WOULD TAKE OVER.
BOTH MEN HAVE CALLED FOR THE
RESIGNATION.
>> 6:36 ON THIS WEDNESDAY
MORNING, PRESIDENT TRUMP
DELIVERED HIS SECOND STATE OF
THE UNION ADDRESS BEFORE
CONGRESS ON TUESDAY LAST NIGHT.
HE URGED LAWMAKERS TO BREAK
WHAT HE CALLED DECADES OF
POLITICAL STALEMATES.
>> I AM ASKING YOU TO CHOOSE
GREATNESS, NO MATTER THE TRIALS
WE FACE, NO MATTER THE
CHALLENGES TO COME, WE MUST GO
FORWARD TOGETHER, WE MUST KEEP
AMERICA FIRST IN OUR HEARTS.
>>'S WORDS FOLLOW THE 35 DAY
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN AND WITH
THE THREAT OF ANOTHER ONE
LOOMING, THE PRISON ALSO
ANNOUNCED PLANS FOR A TWO-DAY
SUMMIT WITH NORTH KOREAN LEADER
KIM JONG-UN IN VIETNAM LATER
THIS MONTH AND HE MADE AN
APPARENT REFERENCE TO THE
RUSSIAN INVESTIGATION CITING
RIDICULOUS PARTISAN
INVESTIGATION.
>> EVEN AS I AM DISAPPOINTED BY
THE APPROACH TO OUR PROBLEM, I
STILL DON'T WANT HIM TO FAIL.
>> BUT WE NEED HIM TO TELL THE
TRUTH.
>> AND TO RESPECT HIS DUTIES.
AND RESPECT THE EXTRAORDINARY
DIVERSITY THAT DEFINES AMERICA.
>> THE DEMOCRATIC RESPONSE AS
YOU HEARD WAS FROM STACIE
ABRAMS WHO LOST THE GEORGIA
GOVERNOR'S RACE LAST YEAR.
SHE IS THE FIRST AFRICAN-
AMERICAN WOMAN TO HANDLE THE
STATE OF THE UNION RESPONSE.
SHE SAID IT WAS A STUNT
ENGINEERED BY THE PRESIDENT.
AND
>>> SAINT ALBANS SCHOOL IS
LOOKING INTO SEXUAL ASSAULT
ALLEGATIONS.
IT HAS NO EVIDENCE OF RECENT
ALLEGATIONS, BUT THERE HAVE
BEEN ACCOUNTS OF WRONGDOING BY
FORMER TEACHERS.
THE WASHINGTON POST REPORTED
THAT A MAN TAUGHT IN SAINT
ALBANS IN THE 80s AFTER BEING
FIRED FROM ANOTHER SCHOOL OVER
SIMILAR ALLEGATIONS.
AND THIS IS SUCH BAD NEWS, MORE
BAD NEWS FOR WIZARDS FANS.
WE ALREADY KNEW JOHN WALL WOULD
MISS A SEASON AFTER GETTING
SURGERY ON HIS HEEL, BUT NEXT
SEASON IS IN JEOPARDY AS WELL.
HE WILL MISS MOST IF NOT ALL OF
NEXT SEASON BECAUSE HE NEEDS
SURGERY ON HIS LEFT ACHILLES
TENDON WHICH HE TORE AFTER A
FALL IN HIS HOME.
DOCTORS DISCOVERED THE INJURY
ON MONDAY.
HE IS SET TO MAKE ALMOST $40
MILLION NEXT SEASON.
>> THAT IS GOOD WORK IF YOU CAN
GET IT.
>> THAT MUST'VE BEEN A BAD
FALL, BECAUSE YOU REALLY HAVE
TO FALL HARD FOR IT TO BE AND
THAT BAD SHAPE.
>> ANY VIEWERS THAT MAKE IT
THROUGH THIS WIZARD SEASON, I
THINK DESERVES A NANCY PELOSI
CLAP.
>> ON THE SAINT ALBANS STORY,
THAT IS MY ALMA MATER AND I'M A
LOVER OF THAT SCHOOL AND I JUST
WANT COMPLETE TRANSPARENCY.
I HOPE THEY DO THE
INVESTIGATION AND THEY GET TO
THE BOTTOM OF IT SO THEY CAN
EITHER CLEAR THE SCHOOL NAME OR
EXACTLY BE AN EXAMPLE OF HOW TO
HANDLE SCANDALS LIKE THIS WHEN
THEY OCCUR.
>> FAR FROM BEING OVER.
>> WE CONTINUE THE WEEKLONG
SERIES ON THE AMAZON EFFECT
ALONG WITH THE PROMISE OF HIGH-
PAYING JOBS, WE GET MORE
EXPENSIVE HOUSING AND POSSIBLY
MORE PEOPLE PRICED OUT OF HOMES
AND SOME PEOPLE ARE FALLING
THROUGH THE CRACKS.
IN SEATTLE, AMAZON IS BASED,
HAVE A HUGE PROBLEM WITH
HOMELESSNESS, AND WILL THOSE
PROBLEMS BECOME OURS?
HERE IS PEGGY FOX.
>> Reporter: IN ORDER TO
UNDERSTAND THE POTENTIAL IMPACT
ON HOMELESSNESS IN THE DC AREA,
WE WENT OUT WEST TO SEATTLE
WHERE THE PROBLEM IS GETTING
WORSE.
>> LITERALLY NOTHING.
>> IN SEATTLE, YOU WILL FIND A
LANDSCAPE LITTERED WITH TENTS.
>> WE HAVE SOME PEOPLE WHO HAVE
FALLEN INTO HOMELESSNESS OR ARE
AT THE VERY EDGE OF BECOMING
HOMELESS BECAUSE OF RENT
INCREASES.
>> HERE IS A QUESTION FOR THE
DC AREA, WILL AMAZON BRING WITH
IT A RISING HOMELESS
POPULATION?
IN ARLINGTON COUNTY, OFFICIALS
SAY THEY ARE WAY AHEAD OF THE
GAME IN CURBING HOMELESSNESS
OVER THE LAST 8 YEARS, THEY
HAVE REDUCED IT BY 64%.
>> WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO IS YOU
HAVE TO MOVE SOMEWHERE FROM
HOMELESSNESS INTO A HOME,
THAT'S 45 TO 50,000 IF YOU ARE
ON THE STREETS AND IT COSTS
ABOUT $20,000 IF WE PUT THEM
INTO HOUSING.
>> WHAT I'M WORRIED ABOUT MORE
IS ABOUT THE IMPACT ON
AFFORDABLE HOUSING HERE, IN
ARLINGTON COUNTY.
>> OUR IDEA, MY IDEA IS TO GROW
THE HOUSING SUPPLY RIGHT NOW
BEFORE THEY EVEN COME.
>> TONIGHT AT 11:00, PEGGY
VISITS A VIRGINIA GROUP WITH A
HIGH SUCCESS RATE OF FINDING
HOUSING FOR THE HOMELESS AND
LEARNS WHAT THE CONCERNS ARE
ABOUT THE AMAZON EFFECT HERE IN
OUR AREA.
>> WHAT IS THE ONE THING TO
KNOW ABOUT THE FORECAST?
>> YOU NEED TO KNOW THAT IT
WILL BE MUCH COOLER TODAY AFTER
HIGHS YESTERDAY, WE ARE IN THE
50s WITH SHOWERS AT THE 2:00.
>> MEMBER THE HORRIBLE CRASH ON
I-695, NOW A TWEET ABOUT IT, WE
HAVE AN ACCIDENT IN THE EXACT
SAME PLACE NOW.
SOUTHEAST SOUTHWEST FREEWAY
PASSING BY THE THIRD STREET
TUNNEL, LOOK FOR AN ACCIDENT
AND DELAYS ARE NOT THERE YET,
BUT THEY WILL GO PRETTY
QUICKLY.
>> IT IS TIME FOR THE MOST EASY
THING WE FEATURE THE PHOTOS AND
VIDEOS AND STORIES THAT YOU
WOULD ONLY SEE IN THIS GREAT
CITY.
TODAY COMES FROM CARLESS.
CARLESS IS A PHOTO OF A JACKIE
SLATER RAMS JERSEY AS A
REPLACEMENT WINDOW OF A CAR.
I AM A LITTLE OFFENDED, HOW IS
THIS THE MOST DC THINK?
IS THIS BECAUSE WE ARE CITY
HOPPING ON BANDWAGONS?
I THINK MOST PEOPLE WERE
GRANDSTANDING ON SUNDAY, BUT
CAN YOU BLAME US?
EVERYONE OUTSIDE OF NEW ENGLAND
AND ORLEANS WAS GUILTY OF THAT.
IF YOU SEE ANY MORE BANDWAGON
FANS, SEND IT MY WAY,
ESPECIALLY COWBOYS FANS, THAT,
I WANT TO KNOW, I'M AT REESE
WATERS ON TWITTER AND FACEBOOK
AND EMAIL OUR WATERS AT
WUSA9.COM.
YOU CAN USE THE HASHTAG TO GET
UP  DC.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY COWBOYS FANS
IN HERE, DO WE?
>> THEY USED TO BEING QUIET
BECAUSE THEY ARE USED TO BEING
IN THE WATER.
>> JUST HAD, I GIVE YOU MY
CLOSING REMARKS ON THE STATE OF
THE UNION.
AND LET'S GIVE SOME MORE LOVE
TO OUR AUDIENCE ONE MORE TIME,
CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY SWIM AND
DIVE TEAM, HERE TO CELEBRATE
NATIONAL GIRLS AND WOMEN IN
SPORTS
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
When was the last time
you felt...
Free.
It's time to uncover
that feeling again.
With the compassion and
strength of a name...
Most accepted by top doctors
and specialists.
And the power of a card...
that opens doors in
all fifty states.
Giving you the freedom to love
to dream to dance
Like no one is watching.
CareFirst
Blue Cross Blue Shield.
Live fearless.
>>> THIS MONTH, WE ARE PUTTING
YOUR HEALTH FIRST, IT'S PART OF
OUR MONTH-LONG HEALTH MATTERS
SERIES THAT RAISES AWARENESS
ABOUT THE IMPORTANCE OF
CHECKUPS AND KNOWING YOUR BODY.
WITH FEBRUARY BEING AMERICAN
HEART MONTH, WE SAT DOWN WITH
ONE HEART ATTACK SURVIVOR WHO
DIDN'T HAVE HEALTHCARE WHEN IT
HAPPENED AND SHE IS THANKFUL TO
BE ALIVE.
>> YOU HAVE THIS EXPERIENCE A
MONTH BEFORE YOUR BIRTHDAY,
THAT'S A REAL WAKE-UP CALL.
>> CHRISTOPHER ROBIN WAS A FEW
WEEKS SHY OF HIS 52nd BIRTHDAY
WHEN HE EXPERIENCED THE MOST
TERRIFYING MOMENTS OF HIS LIFE.
>> AROUND MIDNIGHT, HAD THIS
INCREDIBLE SENSATION IN MY ARMS
AND CHEST.
IT'S AS IF SOMEONE WAS TAKING
THEIR NAILS AND JUST RAKING
THROUGH MY ARM INSIDE AND THERE
WAS NOTHING I COULD DO ABOUT IT.
>> HE FELT A SIMILAR FEELING
BEFORE, BUT THIS TIME IT WAS
DIFFERENT, IT WAS SCARY.
HE KNEW SOMETHING WAS WRONG.
>> IT WAS WORKING ITS WAY DOWN
BOTH BICEPS INTO MY FOREARMS.
THAT IS WHEN I KNEW I WAS
PRETTY MUCH IN TROUBLE.
I CAN ONLY DESCRIBE IT AS WHAT
I CALL THE REAPER'S EMBRACE.
IT WAS PRETTY TERRIFYING, AND I
SAID GOD, I'M NOT READY TO
CHECK OUT, BUT I CAN'T AFFORD
TO CHECK IN BECAUSE I DON'T
HAVE HEALTHCARE.
>> Reporter: BETWEEN JOBS AND
WORRIED ABOUT EXPENSIVE, HE WAS
TRYING TO SURVIVE.
HE WAS RUSHED TO RESTON CENTER
WHERE HE LEARNED ABOUT
BLOCKAGES IN AN ARTERY AND IS
ALL TUBE CALLED STENTS WAS
INSERTED TO IMPROVE BLOOD FLOW.
>> IF YOU HAVE CHECKUPS AND
IT'S COVERED, GO AT LEAST EVERY
SIX MONTHS ESPECIALLY AFTER THE
AGE OF 40, BECAUSE THE
LIKELIHOOD OF YOU HAVING A
SITUATION LIKE I'VE HAD IS
GOING TO BE GREATER AND
GREATER.
>> IS MEDICAL BILLS REACHED
CLOSE TO A WHOPPING $90,000,
BUT GET THIS, HE APPLIED FOR A
CHARITY PROGRAM AT RESTON
HOSPITAL CENTER THAT WAIVED
SOME OF THE EXPENSES.
GETTING TESTS TO CHECK ON YOUR
HEALTH CAN BE EXPENSIVE, SO WE
PARTNER WITH THE SAME HOSPITAL
THAT HELPED SAVE HIM TO MAKE IT
EASIER TO SAVE YOU.
WE OFFER TWO FREE SESSIONS
TOMORROW, ONE AT SEVEN IN THE
MORNING UNTIL NOON AND THE
SECOND SESSION WILL BE FROM
2:00 UNTIL 7:00 P.M.
BOTH AT THE YMCA FAIRFAX COUNTY
IN RESTON ON SUNSET HILLS ROAD.
WHILE FREE, WE WANT YOU TO
REGISTER.
JUST GO TO WUSA9.COM/ HEALTH
MATTERS.
LOTS OF GOOD STUFF HAPPENING,
GIVE ME MORE GOOD NEWS.
>>> WE HAVE COOL WEATHER AND
SHOWERS TODAY.
WE HAD 70s YESTERDAY AND TODAY
WILL BE IN THE 50s ACROSS THE
AREA AND 47 AS YOU STEP OUTSIDE
IN DC.
THE FRONT STALLS ACROSS THE
AREA AND THAT'S THE MAIN REASON
FOR RAIN TODAY.
WE HAVE SHOWERS OVER THE ROMNEY
AND CUMBERLAND AREA AND BY 5:00
OR 6:00, THE RAIN MAKES ITS WAY
INTO THE METRO DC AREA AND
THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS WE
ISSUED THE YELLOW WEATHER
ALERT.
THE EVENING DRIVE WILL BE
SLOWER WITH THE RAIN OUT THERE.
8:00 IN EVENING AND RAIN IS
ACROSS THE AREA.
LATER TONIGHT, WE GET A BREAK
FROM THE SHOWERS AND TO KEEP
THE RAIN CHANCE IN THE FORECAST
FOR THURSDAY AS WELL, AND HIS
WHAT WE THINK TODAY, 48 TO 55
DEGREES WITH SHOWERS AND IT IS
CLOUDY OVER THE NEXT 12 HOURS,
YOU FIND A BETTER CHANCE FOR
RAIN IN THE EVENING AND BY 7
PM, RIGHT AT 50 DEGREES AND
UPPER 40s THROUGHOUT THE REST
OF THE EVENING AND AFTERNOON.
MUCH COOLER TODAY VERSUS
YESTERDAY.
A STRONGER COLD FRONT COMES IN
FRIDAY.
WE TOP OUT IN THE 60s ON
FRIDAY, BUT LOOK AT THE COLD
AIR ON THE BACK OF IT.
BY SATURDAY, A HIGH OF ONLY 39
AND 41 ON SUNDAY.
REALLY QUICK, WE HAVE A CHANCE
FOR SOME WINTER WEATHER THAT
WILL COME OF REARING ITS HEAD
BACK INTO THE AREA.
THAT WILL BE NEXT WEEK.
THIS IS MONDAY, A CHANCE FOR
SNOW AND RAIN AND LOOKING AT
THE MODELS AND LATEST TRENDS
PUTS US IN A WARMER SCENARIO
THAT WOULD GIVE MORE RAIN
AROUND DC AND THE RAIN AND SNOW
LINE HAS MOVED, IT'S FURTHER
SOUTH, NOW IT'S FURTHER TO THE
NORTH.
THIS WILL LOOK LIKE LESS SNOW
AROUND THE AREA ON MONDAY AND
ON TUESDAY, THE LATEST TREND IS
TO GIVE US A MIX.
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE THE BULK OF
THIS STAYS TO THE SOUTH.
SOUTHERN SUBURBS WOULD HAVE A
BETTER CHANCE OF PICKING UP ON
SNOW OUT OF THIS.
WE ARE A WEEK AWAY, BUT WE
STILL HAVE TIME TO FINE-TUNE
THE FORECAST AND JUST KNOW THAT
WINTER WEATHER IS NOT GOING TO
GO AWAY QUIETLY.
IT WILL BE BACK NEXT WEEK.
65 TOMORROW IN 60s ON FRIDAY
AND 39 ON SATURDAY AND 41 ON
SATURDAY AND WE HAVE THE MIX.
>>> A BIG DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
THE ACCIDENT ON SOUTHEAST
SOUTHWEST FREEWAY, TODAY IS THE
EAST BOUND LANE.
THIS IS A LOOK AT THE 14th
STREET BRIDGE WHERE WE SEE
DELAYS IF YOU TRIED TO HEAD
AROUND THE 14th STREET BRIDGE
AND GO TO 395, THAT SOUTHWEST
FREEWAY BECAUSE OF THE ACCIDENT
BY THE THIRD STREET TUNNEL AND
WE HAVE A CLOSURE ON ROUTE 15
IN BOTH DIRECTIONS BY MOUNT
BILL WROTE IN A CLOSURE ON
ROUTE ONE IN VIRGINIA HEADING
SOUTHBOUND.
AND THIS ONE IS NEW AND ANOTHER
CLOSURE, THREE CLOSURES ON
ROUTE FIVE IN ST. MARY'S
HEADING SOUTHBOUND TO THREE
NOTCH ROAD, THIS IS ONE WHERE
WE HAD THE PHOTO SENT OUT BY
THE MECHANICSVILLE FIRE
DEPARTMENT WHO SAID A COMMUTER
BUS AND UTILITY TRUCK WERE
INVOLVED IN THE ACCIDENT AND
TWO PEOPLE WERE INJURED IN ONE
OF THEM WAS A MEDEVAC FROM THE
SCENE WHICH MEANS PRETTY
SERIOUS ENTRIES.
NO ON
I'm a concrete mason.
I had severe fatigue, went to
a doctor.
Became diagnosed with
Hodgkin's lymphoma.
I had to put my trust in
somebody.
We recommended chemotherapy,
and then a stem cell transplant.
When his disease progressed,
I thought that he would be a
good candidate
for immunotherapy
to unleash his immune system
against the cancer.
I'm back to working hard.
I've honestly have never felt
this great.
The evolution of cancer care
is here.
Learn more at cancercenter.com
appointments available now.
IF YOU FEEL LIKE YOU SPEND
TOO MUCH TIME IN THE BATHROOM
WITH RECURRING
CONSTIPATION AND BELLY PAIN
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
AND SAY YESSS! TO LINZESS.
♪ ♪ ♪
YESSS!
LINZESS TREATS ADULTS WITH IBS
WITH CONSTIPATION
OR CHRONIC CONSTIPATION.
LINZESS CAN HELP RELIEVE
YOUR BELLY PAIN
AND LETS YOU HAVE MORE FREQUENT
AND COMPLETE BOWEL MOVEMENTS.
LINZESS IS NOT A LAXATIVE.
IT WORKS DIFFERENTLY TO
HELP YOU GET AHEAD OF YOUR
RECURRING CONSTIPATION
AND BELLY PAIN.
DO NOT GIVE LINZESS
TO CHILDREN LESS THAN 6,
AND IT SHOULD NOT BE GIVEN TO
CHILDREN 6 TO LESS THAN 18,
IT MAY HARM THEM.
DO NOT TAKE LINZESS IF
YOU HAVE A BOWEL BLOCKAGE.
GET IMMEDIATE HELP
IF YOU DEVELOP
UNUSUAL OR SEVERE STOMACH PAIN,
ESPECIALLY WITH
BLOODY OR BLACK STOOLS.
THE MOST COMMON SIDE EFFECT IS
DIARRHEA, SOMETIMES SEVERE.
IF IT'S SEVERE,
STOP TAKING LINZESS AND
CALL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE GAS,
STOMACH-AREA PAIN, AND SWELLING.
SO SAY YESSS!
TO HELP FOR
RECURRING CONSTIPATION.
YESSS! TO HELP FOR BELLY PAIN.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
AND SAY YESSS! LINZESS.
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
>>> IT IS 6:53 AND 45 DEGREES.
HERE IS A WRAPUP OF THE STORIES
STARTING WITH MATT.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT TRUMP
USED THE SECOND STATE OF THE
UNION AS A RALLYING CRY BUT TO
EMPHASIZE THE NEED FOR BORDER
SECURITY AND A TALK ABOUT A
SECOND MEETING WITH KIM JONG-UN
IN NORTH KOREA.
AND DEMOCRATS HIT BACK SAYING
ANY UNITY THAT IS NOT THERE,
ANY DISCORD COMES FROM THE
PRESIDENT, HIMSELF.
>> LET'S CHECK IN WITH OUR
QUESTION ONE LAST TIME, DO YOU
THINK PRESIDENT TRUMP'S STATE
OF THE UNION ADDRESS WILL HELP
UNITE BOTH PARTIES?
RESULTS ON THE SCREEN, MOST OF
YOU SAY IT NEVER HAD A CHANCE.
>>> WE WILL SEE TEMPERATURES
THAT WILL BE MUCH COOLER,
HIGHER AT 53 WITH SHOWERS AND
THE BEST TIME FOR THE SHOWERS
IS AFTER 2:00 TODAY.
>>> 395 IS SLOW OVER THE 14th
STREET BRIDGE BECAUSE OF THE
CRASH ON SOUTHEAST SOUTHWEST
FREEWAY RIGHT AT THE 19th
STREET TUNNEL.
THE RAMP CLOSED, AND ROUTE 5 S.
IN ST. MARY'S BY THREE NOTCH
ROAD, ROUTE 15 IN FREDERICK AND
NORTH AND SOUTH FIND LANES,
SOUTHBOUND LANES AND CONSTANT
CODE ROAD.
>>> IT IS TIME FOR MY FINAL
THOUGHT.
AS MENTIONED EARLIER IN THE
SHOW, PRESENT AND DELIVERED THE
STATE OF THE UNION ADDRESS LAST
NIGHT.
THE PRESIDENT STARTED THE NIGHT
ON A CONCILIATORY TONE URGING
FOR BIPARTISANSHIP AND
COLLABORATION.
A QUOTE THAT STATED OUT TO ME
IS WHEN HE SAID VICTORY IS NOT
WINNING FOR OUR PARTY, VICTORY
IS WINNING FOR OUR COUNTRY.
WHILE THE SPEECH WAS PEPPERED
WITH RED MEAT FOR THE
PRESIDENT'S BASE LIKE ABORTION
AND THE IMMIGRANT CARAVAN,
THERE WERE ALSO MOMENTS OF
REPROACH BUT LIKE THIS CALL FOR
CRIMINAL JUSTICE REFORM AND
LOWER HEALTHCARE COSTS AND
BETTER JOBS FOR ALL AMERICANS.
I KNOW THAT NO SPEECH CAN TOUCH
ON EVERYTHING, BUT I WAS
DISAPPOINTED NOT TO HEAR
ANYTHING ABOUT MASS SHOOTINGS
AND CHILD SEPARATIONS AT THE
BORDER INTO DIRECT DENIAL OF
THE CHARGES IN THE ROBERT
MUELLER INVESTIGATION.
THOSE ARE THREE OF THE MOST
HIGHLY PUBLICIZED SCANDALS IF
NOT THE THREE MOST HIGHLY
PUBLICIZED SCANDALS IN RECENT
MONTHS.
NOTHING WAS IMPERATIVE FOR THE
PRESENT TO USE THE HUGE
PLATFORM TO EASE PEOPLE'S VERY
REAL FEARS AND ADDRESS THE VERY
REAL ANGER.
BUT STILL MY VERY BIGGEST
DISAPPOINTMENT WAS THE OMISSION
OF THOSE WORKERS AFFECTED BY
THE GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
MOST GOVERNMENT WORKERS ARE
DEALING WITH REPERCUSSIONS OF
THE FIRST SHUTDOWN AS THE
COUNTRY STANDS ON THE EDGE,
BRACING ITSELF AROUND 2.
PRESIDENT TRUMP PUNTED ON
GIVING REASSURANCES AND LEFT
GOVERNMENT WORKERS IN LIMBO.
THAT IS UNACCEPTABLE.
THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO KEEP OUR
GOVERNMENT RUNNING DESERVE
BETTER, LIKE ANY STATE THAT THE
UNION, GUESTS WERE FLOWN IN
FROM THE FAR REACHES OF THIS
COUNTRY TO REPRESENT OUR
COLLECTIVE STRUGGLES.
NO FLIGHT WAS NECESSARY AND NO
HOTEL NEEDED.
THEY ARE RIGHT HERE.
THE PEOPLE YOU SEE EVERY DAY
KEEPING OUR DEMOCRACY IN
WORKING ORDER.
JUST KNOW THAT YOU ARE NEVER
FAR FROM OUR THOUGHTS ON GET UP
DC AND YOUR STRUGGLES WILL
NEVER GO IGNORED.
WE WI
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
January 21st is Squirrel
Appreciation Day.
But squirrels aren't the only
ones saving for the future.
That's why A-A-R-P dedicates
today to you.
Yeah, you!
From planning and budgeting.
To getting a deal on your
next trip.
A-A-R-P is here to help you
Take on Today.