>>> STRAIGHT AHEAD, THE DEADLY
ARCTIC BLAST.
TEMPERATURES ACROSS THE COUNTRY
SLIPPING INTO SUBZERO TERRITORY
AND THE WIND CHILLS MAKE IT FEEL
EVEN WORSE.
HERE AT HOME, NOT NEARLY AS BAD
BUT STILL DOWN RIGHT FRIGID.
BUT THERE IS RELIEF ON THE WAY.
>>> BREAKING OVERNIGHT SERIES OF
HOUSE FIRES ACROSS THE REGION.
THE BATTLE TO CONTAIN THE FLAMES
MADE EVEN MORE DIFFICULT BY THE
BITTER COLD.
WE'LL HAVE A LIVE REPORT.
>>> A HEALTH ALERT FOR PARENTS
THE MAKERS OF AN INFANT
IBUPROFEN NOW DOUBLING THE
NUMBER OF BOTTLES BEING
RECALLED.
WHAT YOU NEED TO LOOK OUT FOR.
>>> AND LATER, NEW CLUES FROM
THAT HATE CRIME INVESTIGATION
INVOLVING EMPIRE STAR JUSSIE
SMOLLETT.
POLICE NOW RELEASING
SURVEILLANCE PICTURES OF TWO
PERSONS OF INTEREST BUT THERE
ARE STILL MORE QUESTIONS THAN
ANSWERS.
GOOD DAY AT 9A STARTS NOW.
♪
>>> RATHER WARM PARTY WHAT WE
WOULD HOPE FOR THIS IS WHAT WE
HAVE TO DEAL WITH.
IT'S BEEN THAT WAY FOR THE LAST
MILLION YEARS EXCEPT FOR MAYBE A
LITTLE BIT COLDER THIS TIME
AROUND.
GOOD DAY D.C.
IT IS 9:01, THURSDAY,
JANUARY 31.
>> I WILL SAY THIS FOR ALL THE
PEOPLE WHO SAY D.C. IS SO SOFT
WHEN IT COMES TO DEALING WITH
EXTREMES.
>> YES.
>> I WAS OUT FOR QUITE A BIT OF
TIME YESTERDAY WALKING AROUND.
BUSINESS AS USUAL.
A LOT OF PEOPLE JUST BUNDLED UP
DOING THEIR THING.
ACTUALLY FELT GOOD ABOUT IT I
SAW ALL THESE PEOPLE THAT
WEREN'T LETTING THE COLD WEATHER
SLOW THEM DOWN.
>> I ASKED MY SON IF THEY WENT
OUTSIDE AND PLAYED.
THEY WENT OUTSIDE A LITTLE BIT
FOR SCHOOL.
>> THEY HAD CANCELED SCHOOL SO I
DIDN'T.
>> SORRY.
SORRY TO BRING THAT UP.
>>> ALSO, SHE'S WORKING THROUGH
IT.
>> THEY'RE GOING TODAY.
>>> ALSO AHEAD THIS MORNING FIVE
DOWN, SEVEN TO GO.
ANOTHER CELEBRITY REVEALED ON
LAST NIGHT'S EPISODE OFFED
MASKED SINGER, AND THAT'S NOT
THE ONLY BIG NEWS ABOUT THE NEW
FOX HIT SHOW.
WE'LL HAVE ALL THE LATEST COMING
UP  AT 10A.
ANOTHER NON SINGER ELIMINATED
LAST NIGHT.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO IT WAS.
I'LL TRY TO GUESS.
>> IF THERE ARE ANY REAL SINGERS
THEY'RE CARRYING ON.
9:02.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE WEATHER.
THE TEMPERATURES IN THE NEGATIVE
TEENS IN REGARDS OF AREAS LIKE
CHICAGO AND MINNEAPOLIS SOME
PLACES DOWN INTO THE WELL INTO
THE MINUS 20S.
THE WIND CHILLS MAKING IT FEEL
EVEN COLDER.
HERE'S YOUR WIND CHILLS OUT
THERE RIGHT NOW PARTS OF THE
COUNTRY FEELING NEGATIVE 40
NEGATIVE 50 IN SOME PLACES.
THE ARCTIC BLAST ALREADY BEING
BLAMED FOR AT LEAST EIGHT DEATHS
NATIONWIDE.
THE BITTER COLD SPELL NOT QUIET
OVER BECAUSE THE POLAR VORTEX
CONTINUES TO MOVE EAST.
SO TEMPERATURES IN NEW YORK WILL
COP OUT IN THE SINGLE DIGITS.
PART OF THE MIDWEST FROZEN TO
STANDSTILL.
BUSINESSES AND SCHOOLS STILL
CLOSED AND A LOT OF FLIGHT
DELAYS AS A RESULT.
MORE THAN 800 FLIGHTS CANCELED
OUT OF CHICAGO TODAY.
>> NOW, WHEN THINGS STARTING TO
UP OVER THE WEEKEND THE
TEMPERATURES COULD FEEL
80 DEGREES WARMER IN SOME PLACES
THAN THEY DO TODAY.
>> CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
>> CRAZY.
>> WOW.
I CAN'T WAIT.
HERE AT HOME, IT IS SO COLD MANY
SCHOOLS IN THE REGION ARE EITHER
DELAYED OR CLOSED AGAIN.
BIG REASON CONCERN THE
SCHOOLBUSES WON'T START TUCKER
IS BACK WITH A FIRST CHECK OF
THE FOR FOR.
HOW LONG WE'LL SEE THIS COLD
WEATHER AND WHEN THIS WARMER
WEATHER WILL FINALLY MOVE IN.
>> I HAVE ALL THE ANSWERS.
I CAN TELL WHO IS NOT EXCITED
ABOUT THE WARMUP.
>> WHO?
>> OUR AREA ROADWAYS, BECAUSE OF
POTHOLES.
>> MY GOSH, YES.
>> OUR PIPES.
MAKE SURE THE WATER IS RUNG
THROUGH THEM OVER THE NEXT
COUPLE OF DAYS.
LET'S GET RIGHT TO IT.
BITTERLY COLD TODAY.
IN FACT WE HIT MINUS TWO THIS
MORNING AT DULLES.
THAT'S COLDEST NUMBER OUT THERE
SINCE 2015.
SO COLDEST NUMBERS WE'VE SEEN SO
FAR THIS WINTER ACROSS THE
REGION AS MOST OF THE REGION AND
BY MOST I MEAN VIRTUALLY
EVERYBODY WITH THE EXCEPTION OF
REAGAN NATIONAL IN SINGLE DIGITS
TO START THE DAY.
UP TO 15 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
SO WE'RE CLIMBING.
QUANTICO IS 15.
NAN MASSES SEVEN.
SILL LOWS 9 DEGREES.
THREE IN FREDERICK MOTT MUCH OF
A WARMUP TODAY.
HERE'S THE UPSIDE OF THE
FORECAST.
A LOT OF SUNSHINE AND ARCTIC
HIGH PRESSURE WILL MAKE IT LOOK
BEAUTIFUL OUTSIDE WITH A LOT OF
BLUE SKY BUT AGAIN DON BE FOOLED
BY THAT SUNSHINE WHEN YOU STEP
OUT THE REAL DEAL COLD OUT THERE
WITH DAYTIME HIGHS EXPECTED TO
BE IN THE TEENS AND LOW 20S
ACROSS THE REGION.
MAYBE WE'LL GET TO 24 AT REAGAN
NATIONAL BUT FOR EVERYBODY ELSE
I THINK LOW 20S WILL DO IT.
SO AGAIN TAKE THIS COLD
SERIOUSLY.
THINGS WILL START TO IMPROVE BY
TOMORROW AND BELIEVE IT OR NOT
WE HAVE 60S NOT ONE DAY OF 60S A
COUPLE DAYS OF 60S ON THE SEVEN
DAY FORECAST.
SO THIS IS A TIME OF YEAR WE
HAVE TO WASH OUR HANDS EVERY
MINUTE SO WE DON'T GET SICK,
RIGHT?  BACK TO YOU GUYS.
>> APPRECIATE IT TUCK.
>> 9:04 IS THE TIME.
AROUND THE REGION SOME OF THE
SCHOOL KIDS WHO WERE TREATED TO
A TWO HOUR DELAY BEGINNING TO
MAKE THEIR WAY TO THE BUS STOPS.
PART OF THE REASON FOR THAT
DELAY MAKING SURE THAT THE BUSES
WOULD START IN THIS FRIGID COLD
WEATHER.
FOX5'S MELANIE ALNWICK LIVE IN
SILVER SPRING MONTGOMERY COUNTY
IS READY FOR ITS BUSES TO ROLL.
GOOD MORNING, MEL.
>> Reporter: HEY, GOOD
MORNING, GUYS.
YEAH, WHEN WE WERE HERE EARLY
THIS MORNING IT WAS NOTHING BUT
A LOT FULL OF BUSES AND YOU CAN
SEE GOOD NEWS.
THEY ARE ALL OUT ON THE ROADS
THIS MORNING, GETTING READY TO
GO.
LOOK, I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE WHEN
I WAS A KID, COLD WEATHER, I
USED TO PRAY AND BEG WHEN I WAS
ON THE BUS AT THE BUS WOULD
BREAK DOWN THAT IS NOT HAPPENING
HERE IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY AND
THAT IS THANKS TO SPECIAL TEAM
OF VOLUNTEERS THEY HAVE CALLED
THE COLD START TEAM, THEY COME
OUT WHEN IT IS ULTRACOLD LIKE
THIS WHEN THEY'RE CONCERNED
ABOUT THE CAR BATTERIES, AND
THEY BASICALLY COME OUT, THEY
START UP ALL THE BUSES AND CHECK
TO SEE WHICH ONES MIGHT NEED A
LITTLE BIT OF EXTRA HELP.
THEY GIVE THEM THAT.
SO WE TALKED ABOUT THE PROGRAM
WITH MONTGOMERY COUNTY DIRECTOR
OF TRANSPORTATION, TODD WATKINS.
>> THEY GO FROM ONE COLD BUS
SEAT TO ANOTHER OVER THE COURSE
OF ABOUT AN HOUR AND A HALF.
THE WHOLE PURPOSE TO MAKE SURE
WHEN IT'S ACTUALLY TIME TO HIT
THE ROAD AND PICK UP STUDENTS
THAT WE DON'T HAVE SOME STUDENTS
BUS SITTING IN THE YARD NOT ABLE
TO START AND THEREFORE WE STRAND
STUDENTS OUT ON A COLD MORNING.
>> Reporter: WE WANT TO LET
YOU KNOW ALSO THAT MONTGOMERY
COUNTY IS UNDER A COLD EMERGENCY
ALERT.
THEY'RE ASKING PEOPLE TO STAY
INDOORS IF POSSIBLE.
IF YOU HAVE TO GO OUTSIDE,
YOU'VE GOT TO MAKE SURE THAT YOU
ARE DRESSED PROPERLY.
THAT MEANS MULTIPLE LAYERS.
YOU NEED TO HAVE A HAT, GLOVES,
AND MAYBE A SCARF OR EVEN LIKE I
DO LIKE A TURTLENECK THAT YOU
CAN COVER UP YOUR MOUTH OR YOUR
NOSE OR YOUR CHIN.
IT'S EXTREMITIES THAT YOU HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT.
ALSO, PETS THAT GOT TO BE IN
INSIDE.
YOU CAN FACE FINES IF YOUR PET
IS OUTSIDE IN THIS WEATHER.
ALSO THE COUNTY IS OPENING UP
ALL OF ITS BUILDINGS WELCOMING
PEOPLE TO COME INSIDE AND GET
WARM DURING REGULAR BUSINESS
HOURS IF NEED TOM I KNOW GUYS
WE'VE BEEN TALKING BOWING THE
NEGATIVE IMPACTS OF ALL THIS
COLD BUT I THOUGHT ABOUT A
COUPLE OF GOOD THINGS.
NUMBER ONE IS YOU CAN EACH YOUR
ICE CREAM SUNDAY THAT HOT FUDGE
SUNDAY AND IT DOESN'T GET ALL
MELT TEE BEFORE YOU GET HOME.
NUMBER TWO, YOU CAN WEAR YOUR
PAJAMAS ALL DAY LONG BECAUSE NO
ONE IS GOING TO SEE WHAT'S
UNDERNEATH YOUR COAT IN WEATHER
LIKE THIS.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> GLASS HALF FULL, MELANIE
ALNWICK.
I LOVE IT.
>> MEL TUCKER ADD HE HAD TO IT
TOO.
NO MOSQUITOES IN TEMPERATURES
LIKE THIS.
ANOTHER POSITIVE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> WE APPRECIATE YOUR HARD WORK,
MEL.
THANKS.
NOW GET INSIDE AND GET WARM.
>>> HERE'S THE QUESTION.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE ASKING.
ARE WE A NATION OF WIMPS
KENTUCKY GOVERNOR MATT EVANS
SEEMS TO THINK SO.
AMERICANS ARE GETTING SOFT SINCE
CLASSES WERE CANCELED FOR BELOW
ZERO TEMPERATURES DURING THE
POLAR VORTEX.
DURING A RADIO INTERVIEW BEV
VINCE SAID WHAT'S HAPPENING TO
AMERICA WE'RE GETTING SOFT,
GETTING VERY SOFT.
IF LIFE IS HARD YOU CAN'T JUST
CURL UM IN A FETAL POSITION IN A
WARM PLACE AND JUST WAIT UNTIL
IT STOPS BEING HARD.
THAT JUST ISN'T REALITY.
HIS WORDS.
PARENTS WHO HEARD THE GOVERNOR'S
RANT WERE UPSET.
THEY SAY IT'S IMPORTANT FOR
SCHOOLS TO CLOSE BECAUSE SOME
KIDS HAVE TO STAND OUTSIDE
WAITING FOR THE BUS FOR A LONG
TIME.
>>> NOW HERE AT HOME, WE'VE HAD
A LOT OF DELAYS AND
CANCELLATIONS DUE TO WEATHER
THIS YEAR.
MONTGOMERY COUNTY PUBLIC SCHOOLS
HAVE TO MAKE UP A DAY BECAUSE OF
SO MANY CANCELLATIONS ALREADY.
>> SO DO I THINK THAT WE'RE
GETTING SOFT?  YES, I DO.
DO I THINK THAT WE'RE MORE OF A
NATION CONCERNED WITH
LITIGATION?  YES I THINK SO M
MORE.
BUT MY GREATEST CONCERN IS, WHAT
ARE KIDS A GENERATION FROM NOW
GOING TO SAY.
>> SERIOUSLY.
>> WHEN THEY CAN'T SAY BACK IN
MY DAY --
>> RIGHT.
>> WE DIDN'T GO TO SCHOOL.
WE STAYED INSIDE WHERE IT WAS
WARM.
IT'S GOING TO ALTER THE
LANDSCAPE OF LOOKING BACK WHEN
YOU'RE OLD.
>> PEOPLE THINK ALL I DO REAL
ABOUT STUFF LIKE THIS.
THIS RIDICULOUS.
WE HAVE CANCELED SCHOOL HERE FOR
THINGS AS MINOR WE THOUGHT
THOUGHT IT WAS GOING SNOW.
IT MIGHT GET WET.
WRL DOES IT STOP?  I GET THE
WILL HE TOUCH US IN ALL WHY
SCHOOLS MIGHT BE TAKING THIS HAS
GONE TO THE POINT OF RIDICULOUS.
MY DAUGHTER FINALLY HAD SCHOOL
TODAY.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW TO FEEL.
WE PAID FOR YOU TO GO TO SCHOOL.
I'M HOPING YOU'RE GOING TO GO.
NO FAULT ON SCHOOL OFFICIALS.
I KNOW THEY'RE TRYING TO DO
WHAT'S BEST.
HONEST WHOLE DOES THE ONUS FALL
ON THE PARENTS TO TAKE CARE OF
THEIR KIDS, BUNDLE THEM UP, MAKE
SURE THEY'RE GOOD LIKE OUR
PARENTS DID WHEN WE WERE LITTLE.
I DON'T GET THIS.
>> THE EXCUSE HAS ALWAYS COLD
WEATHER AREAS ARE BETTER
PREPARED FOR THIS DEAL WITH THIS
EVERY SINGLE YEAR.
>> EVERY YEAR.
>> WE HAVE FOUR SEASONS.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY WE'RE NOT
BETTER PREPARED.
>> I DON'T MIND THE CLOSING OF
THE SCHOOLS JUST IF YOU'RE GOING
TO PREPARE IT ADD THE DAYS ON
THE END OF IT MORE SNOW DAYS OR
WHATEVER IT IS.
YOU JUST GOT PREPARE FOR THAT.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW WINTERTIME IS
COMING.
YOU KNOW IT'S UNPREDICTABLE
AROUND HERE.
>> #GOODDAYDC.
BLAZE ME.
I DON'T CARE.
>> GO TO SCHOOL.
>> BACK HOME WHERE I GREW UP
THEY CLOSED TODAY BECAUSE THE
AIR TEMPERATURE WAS MINUS NINE.
FIRST TIME THEY CLOSED.
>> LET'S TURN TO OTHER NEWS
RIGHT NOW BREAKING OVERNIGHT,
LOCAL FIRE CREWS ARE FIGHTING
SEVERAL BLAZES ACROSS THE REGION
IN THESE BITTER COLD
TEMPERATURES AT LEAST ONE
FIREFIGHTER WAS ACTUALLY HURT IN
A FIRE.
THIS WAS IN MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
SELF PEOPLE WERE RESCUED FROM AN
APARTMENT FIRE IN FAIRFAX CO
COUNTY.
BUT OF THOSE FIRES BOTH OF THOSE
FIRES RATHER ARE NOW OUT AT THIS
HOUR BUT THE WEATHER CERTAINLY
MAKING IT REALLY DIFFICULT.
>> NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT THOSE
FIREFIGHTERS OUT IN THE COLD AND
THE FREEZING CONDITIOS AND
FREEZING WATER OUT THERE THIS
MORNING OF THE BOB, JUST
STRUGGLE ON TOP OF STRUGGLE THIS
MORNING.
>> Reporter: YEAH, IT'S BETTER
NOW THAT THE SUN IS UP BUT MOST
OF THE FIRE FIGHTING HAS BEEN
DONE IN THE DARKNESS AND BEFORE
THE SUN REALLY ACTUALLY STARTED
SHINING HERE.
THE FIRE FIGHTING HAS ENDED.
THE INVESTIGATION BEGINS.
YOU CAN SEE THERE ARE FIRE
INVESTIGATORS INSIDE THIS IS THE
GRAND VIEW APARTMENTS.
THIS IS CARLIN SPRINGS ROAD IN
BAILEY'S CROSSROADS.
THIS FIRE THEY TELL ALSO STARTED
ON THE SECOND FLOOR.
IT WENT UP TO THE THIRD FLOOR.
EIGHT PEOPLE HAD TO BE RESCUED
OFF THE BALCONIES HERE.
50 PEOPLE ARE DISPLACED.
WE CAN SHOW YOU SOME VIDEO FROM
BEFORE DAWN THIS WAS CALLED OUT
ABOUT 5:45 THIS MORNING.
OF COURSE, THEY DON'T KNOW THE
CAUSE.
THE QUESTION IS WHERE PEOPLE
HERE TRYING TO KEEP WARM?  A
SPACE HEATER PERHAPS THE SOURCE
OF A FIRE IN GERMANTOWN MARYLAND
EARLIER TODAY.
HERE WE JUST DON'T KNOW.
BUT THEY'RE TRYING TO KEEP
PEOPLE WARM BY PUTTING THEM IN
COUNTY BUSES.
SOME WERE CAMPING OUT AT THE
7ELEVEN DOWN THE STREET.
I HAD A CHANCE TO ASK AN
ASSISTANT FIRE CHIEF HERE IN
FAIRFAX COUNTY THE DO'S AND
DON'TS AS WE TRY TO STAY WARM ON
A BITTER OVERNIGHT LIKE LAST
NIGHT.
>> EVERYBODY WANTS TO TRY TO
STAY WARM, AND WE TRY TO USE
THINGS THAT PROVIDE WARMTH IN
IMPROPER WAYS AND NOT THINKING
ABOUT THE CONSEQUENCES.
IT'S TOKE LEAVE THE STOVE ON.
IT'S NOT.
IT'S NOT WHEN YOU DO THAT.
WHEN WE'RE COLD WE WANT TO BE
WARM.
LEAVING YOUR STOVE ON, USING
YOUR OVEN, USING HEATING DEVICES
IN WAYS THEY'RE NOT DESIGNED
UNFORTUNATELY CAN LEAD TO
SIGNIFICANT FIRES.
NOT TO SUGGEST THAT'S WHAT THIS
WAS, BUT, YOU KNOW, IT IS A
CONCERN IN WEATHER LIKE THIS.
>> Reporter: SO YOU HAD
FAIRFAX COUNTY, ARTICLE COUNTY,
ALEXANDRIA CITY FIRE DEPARTMENTS
HERE.
THEY'RE A LITTLE HOT SPOTS STILL
SMOKING.
THEY ARE KEEPING FIRE CREWS
HERE.
YOU SEE THEM HERE SOME OF THEM
STANDING IN THE SUNSHINE NOW TO
KEEP WARM.
AS THIS INVESTIGATION BEGINS.
AGAIN THEY'RE NOT SURE IF THIS
WAS CAUSED BY A SPACE HEATER OR
SOMEONE LEAVING AN OVEN DOOR
OPEN OR WHAT HAVE YOU.
PEOPLE TRYING TO KEEP WARM IN
THEIR HOMES OVERNIGHT.
BUT WE'LL FIND OUT AT THAT POINT
AND LET YOU KNOW THE CAUSE HERE,
BUT THAT'S BEEN HAPPENING AROUND
THE AREA WHILE THEY WERE
FIGHTING THIS ONE HERE, GUYS, IN
BAILEY'S CROSSROADS THERE WAS
ANOTHER FIRE AT A HOME IN
HERNDON THAT FAIRFAX COUNTY WAS
DEALING WITH THIS MORNING.
>> FEEL FOR ALL INVOLVED, RIGHT.
>> YUP.
>> POLICE IN CHICAGO MEANWHILE
ARE INVESTIGATE A POSSIBLE HATE
CRIME ATTACK ON JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
THERE THERE MAY BE A BREAK IN
THE CASE THOUGH.
COMING UP NEXT ALLISON SEYMOUR
WILL BE BACK WITH THE PICTURES
OF THE PERSONS OF INTEREST.
>> PLUS JUST THREE DAYS UNTIL
THE SUPER BOWL SUNDAY AND
SECURITY IS A TOP PROMPT.
WE'LL HAVE AN UPDATE FROM
ATLANTA LITTLE BIT LATER.
9:12 IS THE TIME.
BACK IN A MOMENT.
♪♪
A lot happens in a day.
Outlast happens once.
Outlast all day lip color
with 24 hour stay power.
Now in custom nudes.
From COVERGIRL.
IT'S LIKE A FRIDAY NIGHT,
WHERE YOU MADE PLANS,
BUT YOU AND YOUR BFF
CHANGE INTO SWEATS
AND FINISH THE
WHOLE SERIES INSTEAD.
NEW TWO GOOD
GREEK LOWFAT YOGURT.
SLOW-STRAINED DOWN
TO 2 GRAMS OF SUGAR.
BECAUSE SOMETIMES YOU JUST GOTTA
DO GOOD BY YOU.
♪
>> 9:15.
CHICAGO POLICE NOW ASKING FOR
THE PUBLIC TO HELP IDENTIFY TWO
PEOPLE SHOWN IN NEWLY LEASED
SURVEILLANCE STILLS.
AUTHORITIES HOPING TO QUESTION
THE PAIR IN CONNECTION WITH THE
ALLEGED ATTACK ON EMPIRE STAR
JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
>> ALLISON SEYMOUR IS BACK WITH
THE LATEST ON THE INVESTIGATION.
ALLISON?
>> WELL AS THE SAYING GOES,
WISDOM, THE SHOW MUST GO ON.
SOURCES SAY THAT FILMING ON THE
FOX HIT EMPIRE WILL RESUME
TODAY.
WITH JUSSIE SMOLLETT RELEASED
FROM THE HOSPITAL.
THIS COMES JUST DAYS AFTER HE
WAS RHEE REPORTEDLY VICTIM OF A
RACIST AND HOMOPHOBIC ATTACK ON
THE STREETS OF CHICAGO.
POLICE STILL DON'T HAVE ANY
SUSPECTS BUT THEY DO WANT TO
TALK TO TWO PERSONS OF INTEREST.
CHICAGO POLICE RELEASING THESE
SURVEILLANCE PHOTOS WEDNESDAY
NIGHT OF TWO POSSIBLE PERSONS OF
INTEREST IN THE ALLEGED ATTACK
ON EMPIRE ACTOR JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
THE PHOTOS DON'T GIVE A CLEAR
PICTURE OF THE PEOPLE SHOWING
TWO SILHOUETTES WALKING NEAR THE
SCENE OF THE ATTACK SOMEWHERE
BETWEEN 1:30 AND 1:45 TUESDAY
MORNING.
IT WAS JUST MINUTES LATER AROUND
2:00 A.M. SMOLLETT WAS
REPORTEDLY ATTACKED BY TWO
MASKED PEOPLE.
WHO WERE YELLING RACIAL AND
HOMOPHOBIC SLURS AT THE ACTOR.
SMOLLETT LATER SAYING THEY ALSO
USED THE PHRASE THIS IS MAGA
COUNTRY.
>> THE COPS ARE APPARENTLY
TELLING SOME METER YA OUTLETS
THEY DIDN'T GET THAT
INFORMATION.
I CAN TELL YOU THAT JUSSIE SAYS
THAT HAPPENED.
>> THE 36-YEAR-OLD ACTOR WHO IS
OPENLY GAY TOLD POLICE DURING
THE ATTACK THE INDIVIDUALS
STRUCK HIM IN THE FACE, POURED A
CHEMICAL ON HIM AND WRAPPED A
ROPE AROUND HIS NECK.
THEN THEY TOOK OFF.
>> JUST CONFIRMS WHAT SO MANY
LGBTQ PEOPLE AND PARTICULARLY
LGBTQ PEOPLE OF COLOR LIVE WITH
EVERY DAY THE THREAT OF
POTENTIAL VIOLENCE.
>> SO FAR THERE'S NO VIDEO OF
THE A ALLEGED ATTACK.
DETECTIVES RELEASE THE THE
IMAGES AFTER REVIEWING HUNDREDS
OF HOURS OF SURVEILLANCE IF THE
TAJ HOPING SOMEONE CAN IDENTIFY
THE PAIR TO DETERMINE IF THEY
WERE INVOLVED.
36-YEAR-OLD JUSSIE SMOLLETT IS
SAID TO BE GOOD SPIRITS.
MEANWHILE, THE FBI IS ALSO
INVESTIGATING A THREATENING
LETTER TO THE ACTOR RECEIVED
PRIOR TO THIS ATTACK.
THERE'S CURRENT AL $2,000 REWARD
FOR ANY INFORMATION LEADING TO
AN ARREST.
I CERTAINLY HOPE THEY DO GET TO
THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
REAL DOLLAR.
>> PACK TO YOU GUYS.
>> AL, THANK YOU FOR THAT.
9:17.
THE GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN OVER,
THOUSANDS OF FORMERLY FURLOUGHED
WORKERS WILL RECEIVE MUCH NEEDED
BACK PAY.
FEDERAL WORKERS WILL GET THEIR
BACK PAY BY TODAY.
THE GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN WAS THE
LONGEST IN HISTORY SOME
EMPLOYEES MISSING TWO PAYCHECKS
DURING THE SHUTDOWN.
SOME PEOPLE HAD TO TAKE OUT
LOANS TO SEEK HELP FROM
CREDITORS AS A RESULT.
MEDICARE FOR ALL SEEMS TO BE THE
RALLYING CRYING FOR DEMOCRATS IN
2020.
CALIFORNIA SENATOR KAMALA HARRIS
SAID THE PRIVATE HEALTH ISSUE
SHOULD END MUCH SHE'S A FAN OF
MEDICARE FOR EVERYONE SO A COREY
BOOKER, BERNIE SANDERS AND
ELIZABETH WARREN.
>> EVERYONE HAS ACCESS TO HEALTH
CARE.
PERIOD.
AND THAT'S WHAT WILL HAPPEN
UNDER MEDICARE FOR ALL.
>> TWO WORDS PUT TOGETHER THAT
EVERYBODY LIKES, ALL AND
MEDICARE.
>> SURE.
>> SOUNDS GREAT.
UNTIL YOU HAVE SORT OF EXPLAIN
HOW THAT IS ACTUALLY GOING TO
WORK.
>> FORMER CEO.
STARBUCKS HOWARD SCHULTZ IS
CONSIDERING AN INDEPENDENT RUN
FOR THE WHITE HOUSE AND THERE'S
NO WAY AMERICA WILL ERADICATE
THE STUDENTS OF INSURANCE SCENE.
HE'S SEEN DEMOCRATS A POTENTIAL
SPOILER FOR 2020.
SOMEONE COULD SYPHON DEMOCRATIC
VOTES AND HAND THE SEAT TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> ALL NEW SEASON OF SISTER
WIVES THIS MORNING THE STARS OF
THE HIT SERIES WILL JOIN US LIVE
FOR A SNEAK PEEK.
>>> FIRST THOUGH LET'S CHECK IN
WITH ERIN AND SEE WHAT SHE'S
WORKING ON.
>> HELLO THERE, GUYS.
NICE LITTLE CLOSE UP FOR YOU
MUCH CREWS INVESTIGATING WHAT
THEY THOUGHT WAS A SINK HOLE.
FIND A TUNNEL TO BANK INSTEAD.
WAIT UNTIL YOU HEAR THOSE THEE
DETAILS.
A WARNING FROM PARENTS WHEN IT
COMES TO INSTANT IBUPROFEN THAT
RECALL JUST GOT BIGGER WHAT YOU
NEED TO LOOK OUT.
WOMAN'S STAR KENDALL COYLE
MAKING HERRING RING SIDE DEBUT
IT GOT AWKWARD VERY QUICK.
WE HAVE THOSE DETAILS WHEN WE
CHECK WHAT ELSE IS MAKING
HEADLINES NEXT.
♪
♪♪
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
Ways to lose
stubborn belly fat:
Metal Vibration Therapy.
( ♪♪ )
(Glass breaking)
(Gasp)
Not cool.
Freezing away fat cells
with CoolSculpting?
Now that's cool!
CoolSculpting safely
freezes and removes fat cells
with little or no downtime
and no surgery.
Results and patient
experience may vary.
Some common side
effects include
temporary numbness,
discomfort, and swelling.
Ask your doctor
if CoolSculpting
is right for you and visit
CoolSculpting.com today
for your chance
to win a free treatment.
(Music blaring)
for your chance
to win a free treatment.
Honey, you know,
some things you can't take back.
It's one of those things...
...unless you got it from ALDI.
Their Twice as Nice Guarantee
means if you're not happy
for any reason,
they'll give you a refund
and replace it.
Well fine, why don't you just
return me then?
But, you didn't come
from ALDI.
I'm sure you'll love
Kevin forever, huh?
One thing you'll never regret
is saving big at ALDI.
Save on select Mama Cozzi's
16 inch take-and-bake pizzas,
now just four ninety-nine.
ALDI. Shop differentli.
9:21.
ERIN COMO IS BACK WITH HEADLINES
THIS MORNING.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
GUYS.
GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
WE'LL BEGIN WITH SOME SHOCKING
NEWS DISCOVERY OUTSIDE A FLORIDA
BANK WHICH IS AN ACTUAL
THE FBI DISCOVERED THE TUNNEL
TUESDAY NIGHT WHEN CREWS ARRIVED
TO FIX A POTHOLE IN THE ROAD AND
THEY QUICKLY REALIZED IT LEADS
STRAIGHT TO THE BANK.
NOT TOO FAR AWAY INVESTIGATORS
FOUND TOOLS INCLUDING AN
ELECTRIC JACKHAMMER.
FBI IS NOW INVESTIGATING THE
SCENE AND SAY SO FAR NO ARRESTS
HAVE BEEN MADE.
>>> THE MAKERS OF INFANT
IBUPROFEN DOUBLING PREVIOUS
RECALL OF THE DRUG.
TRYST PHARMA MAKE THE
CONCENTRATED ORAL SUSPENSION
DROPS SOLD IN FIVE OH OUT OUNCE
BOTTLES IN WALMART, CVS AND
FAMILY DOLLAR UNDER THE STAR
BRANDS.
THE COMPANY SAYS THE PRODUCT MAY
HAVE AN OVERLY HIGH
CONCENTRATION OF IBUPROFEN WHICH
COULD CAUSE KIDNEY FAILURE IN
SOME INFANTS.
SO MAKE SURE YOU CHECK IF YOU
HAVE ANY OF THOSE PRODUCTS AT
HOME.
>>> MONTGOMERY COUNTY POLICE
CHIEF THOMAS MANGER ANNOUNCED
HIS RETIREMENT.
HE'S LED ONE OF THE NATION'S
LARGEST POLICE DEPARTMENTS FOR
15 YEARS.
NOW WHEN HE STEPS DOWN IN APRIL
IT WILL END THE SECOND LONGEST
TENURE OF THE COUNTY'S POLICE
DEPARTMENT.
HE PLANS TO WORK CLOSELY WITH
COUNTY EXECUTIVE MARK ELDRIDGE
TO HIS REPLACEMENT.
>> TV GIRD THREE MAJOR STREAMING
SERVICES AND THE VERDICT NET 96
IS EVERYONE'S FAVORITE.
TV GUIDE DETERMINED THE BEST
STREAMING SERVICE RANGING
NETFLIX NUMBER ONE FOLLOWED VERY
CLOSELY BY HULU AND MA'AM SON
PRIME.
CATEGORIES RANGED FROM COST, YOU
KNOW, ORIGINAL CONTENT,
ALGORITHM, THROW BACKS SHOWS AND
MANY MORE.
>>> AND FINALLY, LISTEN TO THIS
ONE.
WOMEN'S HOCKEY GOLD MEDALIST
MANY KENDALL COYLE SCHOFIELD
MADE HER BROADCASTING DEBUT
WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
THINGS GOT AWKWARD.
ONCE SHE WAS IN THE BOOTH WITH
PIERRE MCGUIRE HE TOLD WE'RE
PAYING YOU TO BE AN AN LIFT NOT
A FAN LIKE ANY GOOD JOURNALIST.
SOCIAL MEDIA CRITICS ACCUSED OF
MCGUIRE OF MAN EXPLAINING HOCKEY
TO HER.
SHE HANDLED IT PERFECTLY.
KEEPING HER COOL FOR CAMERAS.
SHE WAS NAMED A GUEST ANALYST
AFTER BECOMING THE FIRST WOMAN
TO COMPETE IN THE NHL ALL STAR
SKILLS COMPETITION LAST
SATURDAY.
SHE KILLED IT.
SHE HANDLED HERSELF SO WELL.
I WATCHED THE CLIP.
HE EVEN COMPLAINED WHICH SIDE OF
THE ICE EACH OF THE TEAM WAS
GOING TO BE.
I FOUND HIS TONE TO BE EXTREMELY
CONDESCENDING I WAS OFFENDED ON
HER BEHALF, GUYS.
>> SHE'S A HECK OF A PLAYER.
IN THE OLYMPICS DID QUITE WELL.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> WOW.
>> OFFENDED TOO.
>> HOPEFULLY MORE ANNOUNCING
OPPORTUNITIES.
>>> 9:24 RIGHT NOW.
WE ARE GOING TO SWITCH IT UP
FROM HOCKEY TO FOOTBALL RIGHT
NOW ALL ICE ON ATLANTA THIS
WEEKEND AS THE CITY GETS SET TO
HOST THE SUPER BOWL.
WE'LL GET A LOOK AT THE SECURITY
MEASURES IN PLACE TO PROTECT
FANS AND PLAYERS.
ALSO A LOOK AT SOME OF THE FUN
SIDE BETS FOR THE BIG GAME.
>> FIRST, THOUGH, A WARMUP JUST
IN TIME FOR THE WATCH PARTY.
TUCKER IS BACK WITH A CHECK OF
THE SEVEN DAY THAT'S COMING UP
NEXT.
♪
♪♪
>> FRESH AT 10A, ANOTHER
CELEBRITY REVEALED ON LAST
NIGHT'S THE MASKED SINGER.
WE'LL HEAR FROM THE LATEST
SINGER ELIMINATED.
PART TWO OF OUR SIT DOWN WITNESS
WOMEN OF THE REAL.
WHAT THEY TOLD US TO EXPECT IN
THE WEEKS AHEAD.
AND ARIANA GRANDE MAKING A QUICK
FIX TO THAT EPIC TATTOO FAIL.
WE'LL HAVE DETAILS IN THE
CELEBRITY DISH.
AND THEN LATER, J.LO'S TEN-DAY
NO SUGAR NO CASH CHALLENGE.
WE'RE SHARING SOME RECIPES THAT
WILL KEEP YOU ON TRACK.
9:25 IS OUR TIME.
GOOD DAY D.C. COMING RIGHT BACK.
♪
With Expedia,
I saved when I added
a hotel to our flight.
So even when
she grows up,
she'll never outgrow the
memory of our adventure.
Unlock savings
when you add
select hotels to your
existing trip.
Only with Expedia.
♪
>>> OKAY.
IMAGINE DRIVING THAT CAR RIGHT
THERE WITH A USED PUBLIC TOILET
SEAT AS YOUR STEERING WHEEL.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT THAT ACTUALLY
MIGHT BE BETTER THAN WHAT THAT
DRIVER RIGHT THERE IS CURRENLY
DOING.
BECAUSE RIGHT NOW YOU CERTAINLY
ARE RIDING DIRTY.
EW.
>> I KNOW THIS IS REALLY NASTY
ON GOOD DAY D.C. THIS MORNING
I'M GOING TO QUIZ YOU GUYS BASED
ON NEW STUDY CONDUCTED BY CAR
RENTALS.COM.
STEVE YOU HAVE TO EXCUSE
YOURSELF.
>> SURE.
>> HE ALREADY TOOK THE QUIZ
EARLIER ON AVERAGE -- I FAILED
BY THE WAY.
>> ON AVERAGE THE AVERAGE
STEALING OF STEERING WHEEL HAS
HOW MANY MORE TIMES BACTERIA
THAN THAT OF A TYPICAL TOILET
SEAT.
THE SAME, ONE, FOUR TIMES MORE
OR TEN TIMES MORE?
>> I'M GOING WITH TEN SINCE
WE'RE --
>> YEAH, TEN.
>> THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
>> THIS WILL MAKE YOU FEEL
BETTER.
IT'S ONLY FOUR TIMES MORE.
>> OH, SHOOT.
>> THE ANSWER IS FOUR.
ACCORDING TO THE REPORT, THERE
ARE WHAT ARE CALLED 629 COLON
KNEE FORMING UNITS OF BACTERIA
ON AN AVERAGE STEERING WHEEL.
THAT'S COMPARED TO JUST 172 ON A
PUBLIC TOILET SEAT.
SO WHAT IS THE SECOND BIGGEST
BACTERIA COLLECTOR IN YOUR CAR?
IS IT THE AUTOMATIC WINDOW
BUTTON, THE CUP HOLDER OR THE
SEAT BELT?
>> OOH, SEAT BELT.
>> I'M GOING SEAT BELT.
>> WINDOW BUTTON.
>> YOU'RE BOTH WRONG AGAIN.
IT'S ACTUALLY THE CUP HOLDER.
>> I WENT WINDOW BUTTON, TOO
WIS.
>> THAT'S THE ANSWER.
CUP HOLDER IS THE ANSWER.
IT'S THREE TIMES DIRTIER THAN A
PUBLIC TOILET SEAT BUT THE SEAT
BELT MAUREEN IS NOT FAR BEHIND.
2.5 TIMES DIRTIER.
>> OH, GOD.
THIS IS SO NASTY.
>> OKAY.
SO WHY SO NASTY?  WELL, THINK
ABOUT IT.
PEOPLE EAT IN THE CAR.
THEY SNEEZE, THEY COUGH.
AND THE REAL KEY IS ONLY 32%
ACTUALLY WASH THE INTERIOR OF
THEIR CARS ANNUALLY.
EVEN IF YOU DO DISINFECT
REGULARLY THE AVERAGE GAS PUMP
HANDLE CAN HAVE 2 MILLION,
2 MILLION.
WE WERE JUST TALKING HUNDREDS.
2 MILLION CFU'S.
ONE MORE THING TO GROSS YOU OUT.
RENTAL CARS AND RIDE SHARES LIKE
UBER HAVE THREE TIMES AS MANY
CFU'S AS YOUR PERSONAL CAR.
>> NONE OF THAT SURPRISES ME.
>> NO.
>> EVERY TIME WE -- WHEN WE HAVE
BASKETBALL I PICK UP THE KIDS
AND AS SOON AS THEY GET OUT OF
THE CAR I GO GET THE WIPES AND
THE SPRAY.
>> YOU DO.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> EVERY TIME.
>> KIDS, WE'RE TALKING SEVENTH
GRADERS PLAYING BASKETBALL
SHAKING HANDS WITH EACH OTHER
AND THEN GETTING IN MY CAR
TOUCHING MY STUFF.
>> I'M ITCHED IMPRESSED YOU
DISINFECT IT.
>> I'M NOT TRYING TO BE SICK.
>> I DO HAVE DISINFECTANT WIPES
IN MY CAR.
I OCCASIONALLY WILL WIPE DOWN
THE STEERING WHEEL I FEEL LIKE
IT'S GROSS.
>> I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD WIPE
DOWN THE GAS P.M. PUMP NOW OR
>> THE A FRIEND OF MINE HAS A
CLOTH IN HIS CAR HE CHANGES OUT
WHERE HE LIKES -- USE IT TO PUMP
HIS GAS AND THE FIRST TIME HE
DID I LOOK AT HIM LIKE REALLY?
>> WISDOM ARE YOU WIPING DOWN
THE CAR BECAUSE YOU'RE WORRIED
ABOUT GETTING SICK TO PRE SERVE
THE RESALE VALUE OF YOUR CAR.
>> BOTH.
>> I'LL EMBRACE THE FACT IT'S
BOOSTING OUR IMMUNE SYSTEM.
>> EXACTLY.
>> THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
>> WE HAVEN'T DIED YET.
OBVIOUSLY WE'RE DOING SOMETHING
OKAY.
>> I'VE BEEN DRIVING FOR A LONG
TIME.
>> WE'RE ALL AT WORK TODAY.
>> EXACTING.
>> KNOCK ON WOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
TUCKER BARNES LET'S CHECK IN
WITH YOU.
WE'VE BEEN TACKING ABOUT THE
WEATHER ALL DAY.
THE NUMBERS LOOK BETTER THAN
THEY DID THIS MORNING.
>> TUCK, YOU KNOW WHAT WE'VE
ALWAYS TALKED ABOUT GOING
INTERNATIONAL FALLS TOGETHER ON
A FIELD TRIP.
>> YUP.
>> MINUS 44 TODAY UP THERE.
>> DIDN'T I SAY THAT 12 TIMES
THIS MORNING?
>> I YOU WOULD BE EXCITED TO GO.
>> OF COURSE I WANT TO GO WITH
YOU BUT I FEEL LIKE YOU HAVEN'T
PAID ATTENTION TO ME TODAY.
>> I JUST SAID MINUS 44.
>> YEAH.
I JUST SAID PINE US IN 4412
TIMES.
YOU'RE TELLING ME NEWS I ALREADY
KNOW, STEVE.
>> YOU SOUND LIKE AN OLD OLD
>> I DIDN'T KNOW, STEVE.
I THINK IT'S COOL.
>> STEP BACK, TUCK.
DO YOUR THING.
>> HANG ON.
WE'LL TAKE A LOOK AT
INTERNATIONAL FALLS TOGETHER.
>> NO I DON'T WANT TO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> 15 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
WE'RE HAVING A HEAT WAVE, GUYS.
IT WAS 10 DEGREES JUST TWO HOURS
AGO.
SO WARMING IT UP.
DULLES 9 DEGREES.
IT WAS MINUTE US IN TWO THIS
MORNING AT DULLES.
COLDEST TEMPERATURE OUT THERE
SINCE 2015.
14 NOW IN LEONARDTOWN.
14 IN QUANTICO, AND STILL
DOING -- LOOK AT FREDERICK EVEN
9:00 A.M. 3 DEGREES THERE.
SEVEN IN HAGERSTOWN.
JUST NOT GOING TO BE A WARM DAY
NO DOUBT ABOUT IT IT IS GOING TO
BE A BRIGHT AND SUNNY DAY BUT
NOT A WARM DAY.
20S FOR DAYTIME LOW HIGHS.
LOW TO MID 20S FOR DAYTIME
HIGHS.
15 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
MINUS 12 IN DETROIT.
MINUS 20 IN CHICAGO.
ALL RIGHT.
STEVE, LET'S GO DO IT TOGETHER.
MINUS 22 MINNEAPOLIS.
STEVE, CAN WE SEE STEVE?  STEVE
MINUS 45 NOW.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> GOLF CLAP.
>> GOLF CLAP?  I DON'T WANT
PLIGHT.
YES MINUS 45.
>> OBVIOUSLY.
>> MINUS 45 IN INTERNATIONAL
FALLS THAT'S THE ACTUAL AIR
TEMPERATURE.
STEVE, OUR FAVORITE PLACE BIG
TROUT LAKE ONLY MINUS 36.
SO YEAH, WE'LL DO ICE FISHING UP
THERE.
WE'RE LOOKING AT SUNSHINE AND
CLOUD DID HE SAYNESS NORTH AND
WEST PARTLY SO MOSTLY SUNDAY DAY
FOR US TODAY.
A QUIET AFTERNOON BUT NOT A WARM
AFTERNOON.
A COLD AFTERNOON AS MENTIONED
LOW TO MID 20S.
REAL QUICK, I'M FAST FORWARD TO
GO TOMORROW.
SO COLD THIS AFTERNOON VERY COLD
AGAIN TONIGHT.
AND THEN TOMORROW WE'LL START TO
GET THAT WARM AIR STARTING TO
MOVE IN AND WE MAY SEE SOME SNOW
SHOWERS BREAK OUT ACROSS THE
AREA.
NOT EXPECTING A LOT IN THE WAY
OF ACCUMULATIONS BUT THERE'S A
POSSIBILITY WE COULD HAVE LIGHT
ACCUMULATIONS DURING THE MORNING
AND EARLY AFTERNOON TOMORROW AS
THAT WARMER AIR STARTS TO RIDE
IN ON TOP OF THE COLD AIR AT THE
SURFACE.
SO THIS IS WHAT WE'RE THINKING
ABOUT KIND OF PRELIMINARILY
AMOUNTS OF SNOW FOR THE DAYTIME
HOURS TOMORROW.
MAYBE A COATING.
I'M REALLY NOT TERRIBLY
IMPRESSED WITH THIS EVENT BUT
WE'LL THROW IT OUT THERE A
COATING TO AN MAYBE AN INCH.
YOU GOT A BETTER CHANCE OF A
LITTLE BIT OF ACCUMULATION
ACROSS NORTHERN MARYLAND AND
SOUTHERN PENNSYLVANIA.
THEN WE'LL START A GRADUAL
WARMUP.
SO IT IS GOING TO BE BITTER COLD
AROUND HERE THE NEXT COUPLE OF
DAYS.
A LOT BETTER BY THE WEEKEND.
LOOK AT SUNDAY AFTERNOON 56 WITH
SOME SUNSHINE.
THEN GET OUT OF YOUR WAY.
WE'LL BE SINGING AND DANCING
NEXT WEEK GUYS.
TEMPS IN THE MID 60S BY NEXT
TUESDAY.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?  ZERO THIS
MORNING IN SOME SPOTS.
65 BY TUESDAY.
SO STEVE, ARE YOU PAYING CLOSE
ATTENTION?
>> TUCK I HAVE A HOMEWORK
ASSIGNMENT FOR YOU.
I KNOW YOU'LL PASS IT OFF TO
MIKE THOMAS ANY WAY.
IT SHOULDN'T BE TOO HARD FOR
YOU.
I CAN'T IMAGINE IT BEING IN THE
CONTINENTAL U.S. MUCH COLDER
THAN MINUS 45.
HAS IT BEEN COLDER THAN THAT?
>> MY SHORT ANSWER WILL BE YES.
I WILL FIND OUT THE EXACT NUMBER
FOR YOU WHEN I RETURN.
THE COLDEST TEMPERATURE EVER IN
THE LOWER 48.
I THINK IT'S IN MONTANA IT MIGHT
BE MINUS 57.
BUT I'LL DOUBLE CHECK.
>> WOW!
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANKS, TUCK.
>> YUP.
>> THANK YOU.
SUPER BOWL LIII NOW JUST THREE
DAYS AWAY.
AND THAT MEANS TIME FOR BOTH
TEAMS TO GET DOWN TO BUSINESS.
THE PATRIOTS AND THE RAMS BOTH
TALKING THE PRACTICE FIELD.
YESTERDAY MEANWHILE SOME PEOPLE
NOW BILLING THE GAME AS THE
MILLENNIAL VERSUS THE PERENNIAL
IN REFERENCE TO THE TWO COACHES.
NEW ENGLAND BILL BELL LITTLE
CHICK HAS FIVE RINGS AND
33-YEAR-OLD SEAN MCVAY.
>> QUARTERBACKS AS WELL.
>> THAT'S WHERE I THOUGHT WE
WERE GOING WITH THAT.
>> I DID, TOO.
WOW.
MEANWHILE WITH TENS OFFICE
THOUSANDS OF FANS IN ATLANTA FOR
THE BIG GAME ALONG WITH SOME
MAJOR PARTIES PLANNED SECURITY
AS YOU CAN IMAGINE IS A TOP
PRIORITY.
>> YESTERDAY LEAGUE OFFICIALS
INCLUDING D.C. FORMER TOP COP
GAVE UPDATE ON WHAT THEY'RE
DOING TO KEEP FANS AND PLAYERS
SAFE.
>> TSA CONTINGENCY PLANS IN
PLACE.
>> ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT
DAYS IN THE WORLD OF SPORTS IS
FAST APP APPROACHING.
ANTICIPATION IS BUILDING UP AS
THOUSANDS OF SPORTS FANS ACROSS
THE US PREPARE FOR SUPER BOWL
LIII.
THE DAY WOULD NOT BE COMPLETE
WITHOUT THE ASSURANCE OF SAFETY
FOR SPORTS FANS.
>> WE HAVE NO CREDIBLE OR
SPECIFIC THREATS THAT HAVE BEEN
BROUGHT TO OUR ATTENTION
PERTAINING TO SUPER BOWL.
>> NATIONAL FOOTBALL LEAGUE
BEEFING UP SECURITY.
FEDERAL AUTHORITIES ARE SETTING
UP A NO FLY AND NO DRONE ZONES
TO SECURE THE STADIUM.
>> WE WANT OF ONE TO COME HAVE
AN AWESOME TIME AND SEE THIS
AMAZING VENUE WE WANT TO YOU
LEAVE YOUR DRONES AT HOME.
>> DESPITE THE SECURITY MEASURES
PUT IN PLACE, OFFICIALS CONTINUE
TO RELY ON THE FANS AS A
RESOURCE TO HELP ENSURE A SAFE
AND SECURE GAME DAY.
THEY'RE ASKING THE PUBLIC TO
REMAIN EXTRA VIGILANT.
>> THEY SERVE AS THE EYES AND
EARS OF THE PUBLIC SAFETY
OFFICIALS SUPPORTING SUPER BOWL
LIII.
>> THE SUPER BOWL WHICH IS
CLASSIFIED AS A LEVEL ONE
NATIONAL SECURITY EVENT COULD BE
A TARGET FOR TERRORISM.
BUT SECURITY OFFICIALS SAY
THEY'RE CONFIDENT THE DAY WILL
GO SMOOTHLY WITH NO INCIDENTS.
>> YOU CAN REST ASSURED THEY
HAVE THOUGHT OF EVERY
CONTINGENCY AND HAVE WORKED
EXTRAORDINARILY HARD TO MAIN
THIS A SAFE AND SECURE GAME DAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
BIG UNDERTAKING.
>> YEAH.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE WILL BE
THERE.
REQUIRES A MASSIVE EFFORT FROM
NUMEROUS AGENCIES TO GET
INVOLVED IN THIS TO MAKE SURE
EVERYBODY IS IN AND OUT SAFELY.
>> KEEP YOUR DRONES AT HOME,
THOUGH.
>> KEEP YOUR DRONES AT HOME.
>> OKAY.
>> AS WE BARREL TOWARD THE SUPER
BOWL RIGHT NOW A LOT OF BETTING
SET TO TAKE PLACE THIS WEEK
ACCORDING TO ONLINE BETTING SIDE
WILLIAM HILL A LOT OF THOSE BETS
WIL COME FROM PROPER POP BETS.
GIVE PEOPLE A CHANCE TO OUT
COMES OF BIZARRE THINGS HOW LONG
WILL THE NATIONAL ANTHEM BE.
WHO WILL BE WITHIN THE MVP?
ACCORDING TO WILLIAM HILL THE
TOP FIVE PROP BETS BY NUMBER OF
WAGERS SO FAR THIS YEAR ARE...
WILL THERE BE SUCCESSFUL
TWO-POINT CONVERSE.
MOST PEOPLE BETTING YES.
THE RESULT OF THE OPENING COINS
TO, 70% BETTING ON HEADS.
MORE POINTS WILL BE SCORED IN
THE SECOND HALF PLUS OVERTIME.
OVER THE FIRST HALF.
WILL ROB GRANT COULD YOU SKI HAD
ONE OF THE WORSE SEASONS OF HIS
CAREER SCORE A TOUCHDOWN.
BETTERS SAY YES.
OPENING COINS TO --
>> DIDN'T WE ALREADY DO THAT.
>> IS IT HEADS OR IS IT TALES?
>> CHRIS?
>> WE HAVE BOTH.
>> WE HAVE TAILS.
>> HEADS.
>> ON THE SAME SCREEN.
IT ACTUALLY SAYS OPENING COIN
TOSS.
>> OPENING COINS TO TAILS.
>> OKAY.
>> SILENCE.
>> THAT'S WHY PEOPLE BET I
GUESS.
IT COULD BE ANYTHING.
>> IT'S 50/50 WE'LL FIND OUT
TOGETHER ON SUNDAY AS FOR THE
MVP HONORS MOST PEOPLE ARE MANY
BANGING ON RAMS RUNNING BACK TOM
GURLY BECAUSE HE BARELY TOUCHED
THE BALL IN THE PLAY OFF GAME.
HE'S COMING OFF AN INJURY.
>> IF HE'S RESTED UP MAYBE HE'LL
END UP DOING WELL.
WE SHALL SEE.
>> HAVE YOU HEARD ABOUT THIS ONE
PRODUCER THAT WORKED AT A
PITTSBURGH TV STATION KDKA HAS
BEEN FIRED FOR PULLING A LITTLE
STUNT.
SO HE LABELED TOM BRADY ON THE
AIR AS QUOTE KNOWN CHEATER.
THE PRODUCER TOLD IT'S
PITTSBURGH WE CAN HATE THE
PATRIOTS.
WE HATE TOM BRADY A LITTLE WING
FOR OUR FANS.
FRIENDS SET UP A GOFUNDME FOR
KDKA HAS APOLOGIZED FOR WHAT
THEY'RE CALLING AN ORDEAL.
IT'S HEAVY HITTING.
>> I THINK IT'S SILLY.
>> I HOPE ANOTHER STATION PICKS
HIM UM IMMEDIATELY.
>> I MEAN THE STATION -- HE'S
FROM PITTSBURGH ORIGINALLY.
SO HE SAID HE WAS HIS DREAM JOB
AFTER HE BOUNCED AROUND FOR A
LITTLE BIT.
THE TV STATION WE -- IN THIS ERA
OF MAKING SURE WE'RE CREDIBLE
AND ACCURATE WITH THINGS
ESSENTIALLY WE --
>> CREDIBLE AND ACCURATE?  WE
JUST HAD FULL SCREEN THAT HAD --
>> LET ME CORRECT THAT ONE FIRST
OF ALL.
IT'S ACTUALLY NOT A CORRECTION.
BECAUSE WE DID SAY WHILE IT
SEEMED CONFUSING TO US THOSE
WERE THE TOP FIVE BETS THAT WERE
PLACED.
SO TWO OF THE TOP FIVE BETS
PEOPLE BETTING ON THE COIN TOSS.
ON THE COIN TOSS.
>> ONE WAS HEADS AND THE OTHER
WAS TAILS.
>> SECOND BET WAS BETTING ON
HEADS.
THE FIFTH MOST POPULAR BET WAS
HEADING ON TAILS.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE SAYING
TRYING TO CASH IN ON THIS EVEN
THOUGH YOU GOT FIRED.
HE HAS SAID AND HE REPORTED IN
THE ESPN ARTICLE THAT WHATEVER
MONEY WAS RAISED HE WOULD DONATE
TO THE CHARITY OF TOM BRADY'S
CHOICE.
>> OH WOW.
>> HE'S A GOOD GUY.
>> TRYING TO PAY IT FORWARD
THERE.
>> THIS IS A MISS STEP ON EVERY
SINGLE STEP.
THIS STATION DROPPED THE BALL.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
THAT'S LIKE -- BEING FROM HERE
AND ONE OF US CHIRON DALLAS
COWBOYS PLAYER LIKE DUE FUSS.
>> WE LIKE PRAY FOR THAT PERSON.
>> 9:39 IS THE TIME RIGHT NOW.
WE CAN TALK ABOUT SUPER BOWL ALL
WE WANT BUT IT'S NO SUBSTITUTE
FOR THE ACTUAL EXPERIENCE.
SO COMING UP NEXT WE'LL TAKE YOU
DOWN TO ATLANTA TO TALK TO
SAINTS L LINEBACKER DID HE MARIO
DAVIS HOW THE NFL IS TRYING TO
SET AN EXAMPLE FOR SCHOOL KIDS
NATIONWIDE.
♪
THE THINGS THAT MATTER MOST
HAPPEN ONE MORNING
AND ONE CUP AT A TIME.
Our craftsmen begin each day...
...Perfectly seasoning our
Hillshire Farm smoked sausage.
So by simply adding
the right ingredients...
...You can end each day crafting
a perfectly delicious dinner.
Cancer won't wait for
appointments to open up,
test results to come back,
or treatment plans to start.
At Cancer Treatment Centers of
America,
we make time for cancer
patients.
Time to answer questions,
relieve worries,
and turn indecision into good
decisions.
Because cancer won't wait,
and we don't think you should
either.
Call or go online anytime
to set up an appointment with
our team of cancer experts.
Cancer Treatment Centers of
America.
Appointments available now.
When you shop with us, you
know how to score.
But did you know you could be
saving even more?
With the TJX rewards credit card
- every time you shop at
our stores,
you earn 5% back in rewards.
TJX Rewards credit card.
An even better value every day.
♪
>> 9:42.
THE NFL TRYING TO SET EXAMPLE
FOR SCHOOL KIDS AND BUILD
CHARACTER ON AND OFF THE FIELD
TEAMING UP THE UNITED WAY TO
PROMOTE ALL DIGITAL IN SCHOOL
PROGRAM CALLED CHARACTER
PLAYBOOK.
>> JOINING US LIVE FROM THE
SUPER BOWL EXPERIENCE IN ATLANTA
TO TALK ABOUT HOW IT WORKS AND
SHOWCASE SOME OF THE FUN FIRST
OF ALL NEW ORLEANS SAINTS
LINEBACKER DIMARIO DAVIS ON THE
LEFT.
BRIAN GALLAGHER AND JOHN CHA
CHAPMAN.
GOOD MORNING TO ALL OF YOU
GENTLEMEN.
BRIAN I WANT TO START WITH YOU
FIRST OF ALL, WHY DECIDE TO TAKE
THIS PARTNERSHIP TO THE SCHOOLS.
WHAT WAS IT ABOUT THAT YOU SAW
AS A GREAT WAY TO SAY I TO
PARTNER WITH THIS GUYS AND I
WANT TO MAKE THIS HAPPEN?
>> WELL, WE'VE HAD A 45 YEAR
RELATIONSHIP WITH THE NFL AND
NFL PLAYERS, AND AS THE WORLD
WENT FROM BROADCAST TO BROADCAST
AND DIGITAL AND THAT MEANT THE
WAY WE WERE TEACHING IN SCHOOLS
AS WELL, IT WAS -- THEN WE GOT
IN CONTACT WITH EVER FIVE THAT
CREATES THIS DIGITAL LEARNING
MAT FORM, IT JUST MADE SENSE TO
BRING CHARACTER, EDUCATION
DEALING WITH BULLYING AND
CONFLICT SITUATIONS AND CREATING
AN INTERACTIVE MAT FORM FOR
MIDDLE SCHOOLER TOSS PUT IN
SITUATION THAT IS THEY HAVE TO
MAKE DECISIONS TO MAKE BETTER
DECISIONS.
THEY'RE GRADES GO UM.
THEY'RE ATTENDANCE IS BETTER.
JUST MORE CONFIDENT, IT'S
ESSENTIALLY JUST KIND OF A
LEARNING TOOL TO DEAL WITH CYBER
BULLYING AND LIFE BULLYING AND
SCHSCHOOLS WERE THE BEST WAY TO
TAKE IT THROUGH.
THINK OF MIDDLE SCHOOLTEACHER
WHO 22 STATES NOW MANDATE THIS
KIND OF TRAINING, AND THIS TOOL
MAKES IT A PLUG AND PLAY FOR A
TEACHER THAT ALLOWS TO GET HIS
OR HER STUDENTS DIRECTLY
INVOLVED IN.
>> YOU SAID 22 STATESMAN DATE
THIS.
HAVE YOU STARTED IMPLEMENTING
THIS INTO SCHOOLS AND HOW ARE
YOU GOING TO DECIDE WHICH
SCHOOLS OR WHICH AREAS GET IT?
>> THAT'S THE BEST NEWS OF ALL.
SO IT'S BEEN -- IT'S IN 3700
MIDDLE SCHOOLS RIGHT NOW.
350,000 YOUNG PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
THROUGH THESE MODULES AND
BECAUSE OF THEIR RELATIONSHIP
WITH THE NFL AND EVER FI WE'LL
MAKE IT AVAILABLE FOR FREE
ANYWHERE IN THE COUNTRY TO ANY
MIDDLE SCHOOL, ANY HIGH SCHOOL
THAT WANTS ACCESS TO IT.
>> THAT'S FANTASTIC.
>> DIMARIO I WANT TO SWITCH OVER
TO YOU FOR A SECOND.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU REMEMBER
DIMARIO WAS COOL ENOUGH TO JOIN
US HERE IN WASHINGTON, D.C. IN
THE LOFT A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO
WHEN YOU WERE DOING YOUR NFLPA
INTERNSHIP.
IT'S BEEN FUN WATCHING YOUR
SUCCESS.
ME PERSONALLY DIMARIO I WAS
HOPING YOU'D BE ON THE FIELD IN
ATLANTA THIS WEEK I'M SURE YOU
WERE, TOO.
>> IT'S NEVER TOO LATE TO LEARN.
HOW DID YOU LEARN WITH DEALING
WITH THAT LAST CALL AT THE END
OF THE GAME?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I THINK IT WAS, UM, IT WAS
SIPPLED UM BET IN DREW'S LETTER.
HE WROTE A LETTER TO THE CITY
JUST PRETTY MUCH, UM,
DISCUSSING, YOU KNOW, AND
SAYING, YOU KNOW, HEY WE DIDN'T
GET THE CALL WE WANTED, YOU
KNOW, THIS WAS ADVERSITY FOR US,
BUT WE GOT -- DUST OURSELVES OFF
AND WISH THE OTHER TEAM WELL AND
CONGRATULATE BOTH OF THOSE TEAMS
THAT ARE HEADED TO THE SUPER
BOWL AND WE'RE GOING TO DUST
OURSELVES OFF AND, YOU KNOW, USE
THIS AS MOTIVATION TO COME BACK
NEXT YEAR.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT IT IS ABOUT,
YOU KNOW, WHAT WE'RE TEACHING
THESE KIDS IN CHARACTER
PLAYBOOK.
YOU'LL HAVE CONFLICTS THAT WILL
COME UP EVERY DAY IT'S ALL ABOUT
HOW YOU RESPOND TO THEM AND THE
CHOICES YOU MAKE BECAUSE THOSE
CHOICES ARE GOING TO LEAD DOWN
SOME PATH WHETHER IT WILL BE A
GOOD ONE OR BAD ONE BASED ON THE
CHOICE YOU MAKE.
IT'S IMPORTANT FOR THE KIDS TO
LEARN EARLY BECAUSE WE HAVE TO
USE IT AS ADULTS EVERY DAY.
>> REAL QUICK TELL US WHY YOU
DECIDED TO GET INVOLVED IN
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> UM, YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN WO
WORKING WITH KIDS AND EDUCATION
REALM FOR ABOUT SIX YEARS WITH
MY FOUNDATION, AND, YOU KNOW, IT
WAS AMAZING TO BE ABLE TO
PARTNER WITH UNITED WAY TO HELP
WHAT DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM WHICH
THEY OFFERED CHARACTER PLAYBOOK
IT WAS PERFECT.
IT'S TEACHING KIDS HOW TO LEARN
FROM USING EVERY DAY SITUATIONS.
THEY MAY SEE A SITUATION A KID
IS BEING BULLY SOMETHING THEY
FACE EVERY DAY AT SCHOOL, AND
GIVE THEM TOOLS AND OPTIONS THAT
THEY CAN USE TO DISSOLVE THE
SITUATION AND SO THESE REAL LIVE
SITUATIONS BEING ABLE TO MAKE
THOSE CHOICES WILL HELP THEM
IMMEDIATELY CHANGE THE
TRAJECTORY OF THEIR LIVES BY THE
DECISIONS THEY'RE MAKING, AND,
YOU KNOW, SO I JUST THOUGHT BACK
TO HOW IT WAS IN MIDDLE SCHOOL I
WOULD LOVED TO HAVE SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
HAVING THE OPPORTUNITY TO BRING
IT TO MY SUMMER CAMP AND NOW
IT'S AVAILABLE TO EVERY MIDDLE
SCHOOL AND HIGH SCHOOL FOR FREE,
YOU KNOW, I WANT TO TRY TO GET
TO EVERY SCHOOL IN MY STATE.
>> I THINK IT'S VERY COOL TO
HAVE THE OPTION THAT'S OUT
THERE.
JOHN, OOH ILL GIVE YOU A FINAL
WORD HERE BECAUSE I KNOW THIS IS
SOMETHING THAT YOU'RE VERY PROUD
OF AS WELL.
WITH THIS PARTNERSHIP WITH THE
LEAGUE.
WHERE WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE THIS
GO?  IF WE COULD LOOK INTO THE
FUTURE NOW AS FAR AS WHAT A GOAL
MIGHT BE.
>> WELL, WE'RE REALLY EXCITED
ABOUT THE PARTNERSHIP AS BRINE
MENTIONED WE'RE IN 3700 MIDDLE
SCHOOLS TO DATE.
WE'D LIKING TO 92 AS MANY AS
POSSIBLE.
TODAY WE REACH 25,000K12
SCHOOLS.
WE'RE DISTRICT BASED COMPANY.
WE WERE BORN AND RAISED THERE.
WE STILL ARE THERE TODAY.
AND I'D LOVE TO SEE CHARACTER
PLAYBOOK USED AS MANY SCHOOLS
ACROSS THE COUNTRY AS POSSIBLE.
NOW THAT IT'S FREE OF CHARGE,
THE OPPORTUNITY IS THERE.
>> AMAZING.
IT'S GREAT.
>> DIMARIO, CAN YOU ROOT FOR THE
RAMS IN THIS GAME OR ARE YOU
JUST LOOKING FOR A GOOD GAME
OVERALL?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> JUST GOING TO BE A GOOD GAME
OVERALL.
I LOVE OF THE GAME OF FOOTBALL.
I CAN'T ROOT FOR ANYBODY.
BUT, YOU KNOW, TWO GREAT TEAMS
GOING TO BE AMAZING GAME.
I'M EXCITED TO SEE IT.
>> WE'RE ROOTING FOR YOU AND THE
SAINTS NEXT YEAR HOPEFULLY
YOU'LL OVERCOME THAT CALL.
GET BACK THERE AND USE IT MORE
OF FOR MOTIVATION JUST LIKE
WE'RE TRYING TO SHOW THE KIDS
THEY CAN DO IN EVERY DAY LIVE.
GENTLEMEN, WE THANK YOU FOR
JOINING US HERE IN, WHAT.
ENJOY THE FESTIVITIES DOWN IN AT
LAND FOR US.
>> THANKS VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> FANTASTIC.
THE INFORMATION IS AVAILABLE
ONLINE.
IF SCHOOLS ARE INTERESTED AS
WELL BUT NICE FREE.
>> I KNOW CAN GET IT.
GO ON THERE AND GET IT IT'S
FREE.
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT.
OBVIOUSLY.
>> SURE IS.
>> ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU HEAR
FOLKS LIKE LEADER OF THE NFL
SAYING IT COULD HELP ME BACK IN
THE DAY.
>> TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IT FOR THE
YOUNGSTERS OUT THERE NOW.
>> 9:48.
SEND IT BACK OVER TO MAUREEN.
>> THANK YOU.
THAT MEANS IT'S COFFEE TIME ON
GOOD DAY D.C.
LET'S DO IT.
IF YOU'VE BEEN EYEING OUR COOL
GOOD DAY MUGS WE HAVE A NEW GOOD
DAY DUNKIN' DONUTS MUG TO GIVE
AWAY PERFECT CUP FOR THAT GREAT
DUNKIN' DONUTS COFFEE.
HEAD TO FOXDC.COM/CONTESTS TO
ENTER OUR MUG CONTEST.
ONE LUCKY WINNER WILL BE
SELECTED BY RANDOM DRAWING BUT
HURRY YOU ONLY HAVE FROM NOW
UNTIL 11AM TO ENTER.
>>> WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
♪♪
>> EVERYBODY IS CONTRIBUTING.
WE CONTRIBUTE AS A WHOLE.
I'VE ALWAYS FELT LIKE WE WERE
ALL INVOLVED IN BRINGING OUR
EFFORTS TO THE TABLE TO SUPPORT
THE FAMILY.
>> I'M SORRY.
I WISH WE HAD THE MONEY RIGHT
NOW.
>> NO IT'S OKAY.
>> IT'S NOT OKAY.
>> I REALLY WISH WE DID.
BUT I HAVE TO GO FIGURE
>> IT'S NOT OKAY.
SOMETHING ELSE OUT.
BUT I HAVE TO GO FIGURE
>> BUT YOU KNOW THAT THIS ISN'T
SOMETHING ELSE OUT.
PERSONAL.
>> BUT YOU KNOW THAT THIS ISN'T
THIS IS -- REALLY DON'T HAVE --
PERSONAL.
LEAK YOU KNOW WHAT OUR TAX BILL
THIS IS -- REALLY DON'T HAVE --
S.
LEAK YOU KNOW WHAT OUR TAX BILL
>> THEN I HAVE TO GO FIGURE
S.
SOMETHING OUT.
>> THEN I HAVE TO GO FIGURE
>> ALL RIGHT.
SOMETHING OUT.
THAT'S A CLIP FROM THE TLC HIT
>> ALL RIGHT.
SISTER WIVES.
THAT'S A CLIP FROM THE TLC HIT
IF YOU'VE NEVER SEEN IT, IT
SISTER WIVES.
FOLLOWS CODY BROWN AND HIS FOUR
IF YOU'VE NEVER SEEN IT, IT
WIVES MARY, JONELLE, CHRISTINE
FOLLOWS CODY BROWN AND HIS FOUR
AND ROBIN AND THEY'RE 18
WIVES MARY, JONELLE, CHRISTINE
CHILDREN.
AND ROBIN AND THEY'RE 18
ALL NEW SEASON IT'S UNDERWAY
CHILDREN.
RIGHT NOW AND IT'S FULL OF
ALL NEW SEASON IT'S UNDERWAY
DRAMA.
RIGHT NOW AND IT'S FULL OF
THIS MORNING THE STARS JOINING
DRAMA.
US LIVE WITH A SNEAK PEEK WHAT
THIS MORNING THE STARS JOINING
FANS CAN EXPECT.
US LIVE WITH A SNEAK PEEK WHAT
GOOD MORNING TO ALL OF YOU.
FANS CAN EXPECT.
>> GOOD MORNING MAUREEN.
GOOD MORNING TO ALL OF YOU.
>> I'M LOOKING AT THE
>> GOOD MORNING MAUREEN.
EXPRESSIONS ON YOUR FACE.
>> I'M LOOKING AT THE
ARE YOU SURPRISED BECAUSE OF THE
EXPRESSIONS ON YOUR FACE.
CLIP OR MY INTRO?  I'M CURIOUS.
ARE YOU SURPRISED BECAUSE OF THE
>> WE'VE GOT A BIG FAMILY, AND
CLIP OR MY INTRO?  I'M CURIOUS.
WE'RE DOING A BUNCH OF STUFF AND
>> WE'VE GOT A BIG FAMILY, AND
SO THERE'S ALWAYS GOING TO BE --
WE'RE DOING A BUNCH OF STUFF AND
>> THE DRAMA.
SO THERE'S ALWAYS GOING TO BE --
>> LITTLE BIT OF DRAMA.
>> THE DRAMA.
>> THAT WORD DRAMA.
>> LITTLE BIT OF DRAMA.
>> UH-HUH.
>> THAT WORD DRAMA.
>> WE GOT YOU.
>> UH-HUH.
>> IT'S ALMOST A CLICHE IN THE
>> WE GOT YOU.
FAMILY DRAMA, DRAMA, DRAMA IT'S
>> IT'S ALMOST A CLICHE IN THE
REALLY FUNNY BECAUSE OUR LIVES
FAMILY DRAMA, DRAMA, DRAMA IT'S
ARE FAIRLY NORMAL.
REALLY FUNNY BECAUSE OUR LIVES
WE'RE FLAWED PEOPLE LIKE THE
ARE FAIRLY NORMAL.
REST OF YOU.
WE'RE FLAWED PEOPLE LIKE THE
[ LAUGHTER ]
REST OF YOU.
>> THE DRAMA JUST ERUPTS
[ LAUGHTER ]
SOMETIMES AND IT MAKES VERY
>> THE DRAMA JUST ERUPTS
INTERESTING.
SOMETIMES AND IT MAKES VERY
>> SOMETIMES ZIMMERLY VOLCANOES
INTERESTING.
A LITTLE BIT.
>> SOMETIMES ZIMMERLY VOLCANOES
>> I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S EXTREME
A LITTLE BIT.
BUT, YEAH.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S EXTREME
OF ONCE IN AWHILE I WANT TO
BUT, YEAH.
SWEAR UNDER MY BREATH.
OF ONCE IN AWHILE I WANT TO
>> OH MY GOSH.
SWEAR UNDER MY BREATH.
>> OTHER TIMES I WANT TO SPROUT
>> OH MY GOSH.
LOVE.
>> OTHER TIMES I WANT TO SPROUT
I LOVE YOU.
LOVE.
OTHER TIMES IT'S --
I LOVE YOU.
>> THE THING CODY A LOT OF
OTHER TIMES IT'S --
PEOPLE WHO AREN'T USED TO THIS
>> THE THING CODY A LOT OF
THEY LOOK AT YOUR FAMILY AND
PEOPLE WHO AREN'T USED TO THIS
YOU'RE SAYING YOU KNOW YOU'RE
THEY LOOK AT YOUR FAMILY AND
FAIRLY NORMAL FAMILY BUT PEOPLE
YOU'RE SAYING YOU KNOW YOU'RE
LOOK AT YOU WITH THE FOUR WIVES.
FAIRLY NORMAL FAMILY BUT PEOPLE
THEY'RE THINKING, HOW IN THE
LOOK AT YOU WITH THE FOUR WIVES.
WORLD FIRST OF ALL FROM A
THEY'RE THINKING, HOW IN THE
FINANCIAL STANDPOINT FROM
WORLD FIRST OF ALL FROM A
EMOTIONAL STANDPOINT, HOW DO YOU
FINANCIAL STANDPOINT FROM
MAKE IT WORK?  YOU KNOW FROM THE
EMOTIONAL STANDPOINT, HOW DO YOU
CLIP YOU DO SEE THE DRAMA
MAKE IT WORK?  YOU KNOW FROM THE
UNFOLDING.
CLIP YOU DO SEE THE DRAMA
SO IT'S NATURAL FOR TO US THINK
UNFOLDING.
THIS WOULD BE A MESS.
SO IT'S NATURAL FOR TO US THINK
BUT YOU'RE SAYING IT'S NOT.
THIS WOULD BE A MESS.
>> WELL, THE THING IT'S NOT A
BUT YOU'RE SAYING IT'S NOT.
CONSTANT DRAMA SO WHAT YOU GET,
>> WELL, THE THING IT'S NOT A
DEFINITELY THE SHOW IS REAL FOR
CONSTANT DRAMA SO WHAT YOU GET,
OUR LIVES.
DEFINITELY THE SHOW IS REAL FOR
YOU KNOW, IT SHOWS THINGS THAT
OUR LIVES.
HAPPEN IN OUR LIVES.
YOU KNOW, IT SHOWS THINGS THAT
AND WHAT WE LIKE IS THAT YOU
HAPPEN IN OUR LIVES.
GENERALLY SEE THE WHOLE FAMILY
AND WHAT WE LIKE IS THAT YOU
THAT WORKING TOGETHER BUT YOU
GENERALLY SEE THE WHOLE FAMILY
DEFINITELY SEE THE DRAMATIC
THAT WORKING TOGETHER BUT YOU
POINTS BECAUSE IT HAS TO BE
DEFINITELY SEE THE DRAMATIC
INTERESTING.
POINTS BECAUSE IT HAS TO BE
>> OF COURSE.
INTERESTING.
>> I THINK IT'S PRETTY GOOD
>> OF COURSE.
REPRESENTATION OF IT.
>> I THINK IT'S PRETTY GOOD
>> IF YOU DON'T GET OUR DRAMA,
REPRESENTATION OF IT.
THEN WE'D BE BORING JUST LIKE
>> IF YOU DON'T GET OUR DRAMA,
EVERY DAY,.
THEN WE'D BE BORING JUST LIKE
>> WE DON'T WANT BE LIKE EVERY
EVERY DAY,.
DAY.
>> WE DON'T WANT BE LIKE EVERY
WE WON'T EVERY DAY.
DAY.
THAT IS VERY VERY BORING MUCH
WE WON'T EVERY DAY.
IT'S NICE TO HAVE HIGHLIGHTS AND
THAT IS VERY VERY BORING MUCH
PUNCTUATIONS.
IT'S NICE TO HAVE HIGHLIGHTS AND
>> I THINK WHEN YOU JUST HAVE AS
PUNCTUATIONS.
MANY PERSONALITIES AS WE HAVE
>> I THINK WHEN YOU JUST HAVE AS
YOU NATURALLY GET INTERACTIONS
MANY PERSONALITIES AS WE HAVE
SOMETIMES WE RUB AGAINST EACH
YOU NATURALLY GET INTERACTIONS
OTHER, YOU KNOW.
SOMETIMES WE RUB AGAINST EACH
>> WE ALSO HAVE DRAMATIC PEOPLE
OTHER, YOU KNOW.
IN THE FAMILY.
>> WE ALSO HAVE DRAMATIC PEOPLE
CHRISTINE IS VERY DRAMATIC.
IN THE FAMILY.
>> YOU'RE SO DRAMATIC.
CHRISTINE IS VERY DRAMATIC.
>> HER DAUGHTERS ARE VERY
>> YOU'RE SO DRAMATIC.
DRAMATIC.
>> HER DAUGHTERS ARE VERY
>> THAT'S TRUE.
DRAMATIC.
>> THEY ARE.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> BUT I'M CURIOUS, HOW DOES
>> THEY ARE.
THIS FAMILY UNIT CAME TOGETHER
>> BUT I'M CURIOUS, HOW DOES
OF FOR THOSE WHO HAVE NOT SEEN
THIS FAMILY UNIT CAME TOGETHER
THE SHOW AND WANTING TO JUMP IN
OF FOR THOSE WHO HAVE NOT SEEN
HOW DID THIS FAMILY COME TO BE?
THE SHOW AND WANTING TO JUMP IN
CODY, WERE YOU MARRIED TO ONE
HOW DID THIS FAMILY COME TO BE?
WOMAN AND THEN THE OTHERS CAME?
CODY, WERE YOU MARRIED TO ONE
YOU MET THE OTHERS AND THEY CAME
WOMAN AND THEN THE OTHERS CAME?
NOT FAMILY?  HOW DID IT HAPPEN?
YOU MET THE OTHERS AND THEY CAME
IT MIGHT BE COMPLICATED IF YOU
NOT FAMILY?  HOW DID IT HAPPEN?
COULD SIMPLIFY HOW THIS FAMILY
IT MIGHT BE COMPLICATED IF YOU
CAME TO BE.
COULD SIMPLIFY HOW THIS FAMILY
>> YOU JUST SAID IT EXACTLY HOW
CAME TO BE.
IT IS.
>> YOU JUST SAID IT EXACTLY HOW
IT'S COMPLICATED.
IT IS.
IT HAPPENS LIKE A REGULAR FA
IT'S COMPLICATED.
FAMILY.
IT HAPPENS LIKE A REGULAR FA
IT JUST SLOWLY HAPPENED.
FAMILY.
SO YOU KNOW WE STARTED WITH MARY
IT JUST SLOWLY HAPPENED.
AND I, WE HAD A MARRIAGE, AND
SO YOU KNOW WE STARTED WITH MARY
THAT EVENTUALLY JONELLE CAME
AND I, WE HAD A MARRIAGE, AND
INTO THE FAMILY AND WE HAD --
THAT EVENTUALLY JONELLE CAME
CHRISTINE CAME INTO THE FAMILY
INTO THE FAMILY AND WE HAD --
WE HAD SOME CHILDREN.
CHRISTINE CAME INTO THE FAMILY
>> EVERY SINGLE WIFE THAT COMES
WE HAD SOME CHILDREN.
IN IT'S BY INSPIRATION AND ALL
>> EVERY SINGLE WIFE THAT COMES
OF THE OTHER WIVES THAT ARE
IN IT'S BY INSPIRATION AND ALL
ALREADY IN THE FAMILY APPROVE OF
OF THE OTHER WIVES THAT ARE
THAT WIFE, AND IT'S A PROCESS.
ALREADY IN THE FAMILY APPROVE OF
THE WOMAN THAT -- EACH ONE OF US
THAT WIFE, AND IT'S A PROCESS.
DECIDED TO COME INTO THIS FAMILY
THE WOMAN THAT -- EACH ONE OF US
IT'S ALL A CHOICE.
DECIDED TO COME INTO THIS FAMILY
AND, YOU KNOW, EACH OF US FELL
IT'S ALL A CHOICE.
IN LOVE WITH CODY.
AND, YOU KNOW, EACH OF US FELL
EACH OF US FELL IN LOVE WITH THE
IN LOVE WITH CODY.
FAMILY.
EACH OF US FELL IN LOVE WITH THE
IT'S A REAL PROCESS AND IT'S
FAMILY.
VERY MUCH, YOU KNOW, BY
IT'S A REAL PROCESS AND IT'S
INSPIRATION, BY SPIRITUAL
VERY MUCH, YOU KNOW, BY
GUIDANCE.
INSPIRATION, BY SPIRITUAL
>> IT'S SERENDIPITOUS.
GUIDANCE.
>> WE NEVER -- WE NEVER -- GO
>> IT'S SERENDIPITOUS.
AHEAD, PLEASE FINISH.
>> WE NEVER -- WE NEVER -- GO
>> GO AHEAD.
AHEAD, PLEASE FINISH.
>> I JUST GOING TO SAY WE NEVER
>> GO AHEAD.
WERE GOING, HEY, WE'VE GOT TO
>> I JUST GOING TO SAY WE NEVER
GET ANOTHER WIFE IN THE FAMILY.
WERE GOING, HEY, WE'VE GOT TO
WE NEVER HAD THAT THOUGHT
GET ANOTHER WIFE IN THE FAMILY.
PROCESS.
WE NEVER HAD THAT THOUGHT
IT JUST HAPPENED NATURALLY,
PROCESS.
UM --
IT JUST HAPPENED NATURALLY,
>> IT WAS BECAUSE MARY AND CODY
UM --
AS PART OF AFORE RELIGIOUS
>> IT WAS BECAUSE MARY AND CODY
BELIEFS MARY AND CODY KNEW THEY
AS PART OF AFORE RELIGIOUS
WERE GOING TO LIVE THROUGH A
BELIEFS MARY AND CODY KNEW THEY
MARRIAGE WHEN THEY GOT MARRIED.
WERE GOING TO LIVE THROUGH A
>> WE HAVE A COUPLE SECONDS
MARRIAGE WHEN THEY GOT MARRIED.
LEFT.
>> WE HAVE A COUPLE SECONDS
FOR ANYONE THINKING ABOUT WHY
LEFT.
SHOULD I WATCH THIS SHOW.
FOR ANYONE THINKING ABOUT WHY
I KNOW YOU SAID YOU REALLY ARE A
SHOULD I WATCH THIS SHOW.
NORMAL FAMILY BUT MAKE THE PITCH
I KNOW YOU SAID YOU REALLY ARE A
FOR ME.
NORMAL FAMILY BUT MAKE THE PITCH
WHY SHOULD WE WATCH THIS HAVE
FOR ME.
WHAT IS IT BEYOND SEEING SOME
WHY SHOULD WE WATCH THIS HAVE
DUDES MIGHT BE LIKE HEY, HE GOT
WHAT IS IT BEYOND SEEING SOME
FOUR WIVES.
DUDES MIGHT BE LIKE HEY, HE GOT
THAT A BOY.
FOUR WIVES.
WHY SHOULD PEOPLE WATCH THIS
THAT A BOY.
SHOW AND GET END GROSS IN YOUR
WHY SHOULD PEOPLE WATCH THIS
FMILY DYNAMICS IN LIFE.
SHOW AND GET END GROSS IN YOUR
>> IT'S NOT ABOUT THE AT AT A
FMILY DYNAMICS IN LIFE.
BOY FOUR WIVES THING.
>> IT'S NOT ABOUT THE AT AT A
IT'S ABOUT A FAMILY EXPERIENCE.
BOY FOUR WIVES THING.
SO WHAT I WOULD TELL YOU IS IF
IT'S ABOUT A FAMILY EXPERIENCE.
YOU WANT GOOD FAMILY PRO
SO WHAT I WOULD TELL YOU IS IF
PROGRAMMING, WE'RE GOOD FAMILY
YOU WANT GOOD FAMILY PRO
FOR THAT.
PROGRAMMING, WE'RE GOOD FAMILY
WE'RE A LITTLE DIFFERENT THAN
FOR THAT.
ANYBODY ELSE BUT IT'S VERY
WE'RE A LITTLE DIFFERENT THAN
NORMAL FAMILY EXPERIENCES.
ANYBODY ELSE BUT IT'S VERY
>> WHEN WE FIRST STARTED DOING
NORMAL FAMILY EXPERIENCES.
THE SHOW, IT WAS TWO OPEN MINDS
>> WHEN WE FIRST STARTED DOING
TO SHOW PEOPLE PLURAL FAMILIES
THE SHOW, IT WAS TWO OPEN MINDS
ARE FAMILIES AND WE'RE JUST LIKE
TO SHOW PEOPLE PLURAL FAMILIES
EVERYBODY ELSE IN THAT WE
ARE FAMILIES AND WE'RE JUST LIKE
LOVE -- WE HAVE UPS AND DOWNS.
EVERYBODY ELSE IN THAT WE
WE CARE ABOUT OUR KIDS.
LOVE -- WE HAVE UPS AND DOWNS.
WE'RE WORKING IT OUT.
WE CARE ABOUT OUR KIDS.
>> RIGHT.
WE'RE WORKING IT OUT.
>> WE WORK HARD ALTOGETHER TO
>> RIGHT.
FIGURE IT OUT.
>> WE WORK HARD ALTOGETHER TO
>> YOU DO.
FIGURE IT OUT.
>> ACTUALLY DID THIS SO SHE
>> YOU DO.
COULD SHOW OTHER PLURAL FAM
>> ACTUALLY DID THIS SO SHE
FAMILIES, THAT PLURAL FAMILIES
COULD SHOW OTHER PLURAL FAM
ARE PEOPLE TOO THAT'S WHAT WE
FAMILIES, THAT PLURAL FAMILIES
CONTINUE TO ALWAYS TRY TO STRIVE
ARE PEOPLE TOO THAT'S WHAT WE
TO SHOW IS THAT MUR FAMILIES ARE
CONTINUE TO ALWAYS TRY TO STRIVE
A FAMILIAR TOOL.
TO SHOW IS THAT MUR FAMILIES ARE
>> THEY ARE WRAPPING ME HARD.
A FAMILIAR TOOL.
I DO APPRECIATE YOU GUYS SHARING
>> THEY ARE WRAPPING ME HARD.
TIME WITH US.
I DO APPRECIATE YOU GUYS SHARING
A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE CONFUSED
TIME WITH US.
ABOUT IT.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE CONFUSED
WHEN YOU WATCH YOUR SHOW YOU'RE
ABOUT IT.
RIGHT THEY WILL SEE A DIFFERENT
WHEN YOU WATCH YOUR SHOW YOU'RE
DYNAMIC A DIFFERENT FAMILY AND
RIGHT THEY WILL SEE A DIFFERENT
COME TO BETTER UNDERSTANDING
DYNAMIC A DIFFERENT FAMILY AND
WHICH IS WHAT WE HOPE TO DO IN
COME TO BETTER UNDERSTANDING
THIS WORLD WITH ANYTHING THAT
WHICH IS WHAT WE HOPE TO DO IN
WE'RE NOT FAMILIAR WITH.
THIS WORLD WITH ANYTHING THAT
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE'RE NOT FAMILIAR WITH.
JUST REMINDER YOU CAN CATCH ALL
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
NEW EPISODES OF SISTER WIVES
JUST REMINDER YOU CAN CATCH ALL
SUNDAYS AT 8:00 ONLY ONLY TLC.
NEW EPISODES OF SISTER WIVES
WITH THAT, IT IS 9:57.
SUNDAYS AT 8:00 ONLY ONLY TLC.
GOOD DAY COMING BACK WITH THE
WITH THAT, IT IS 9:57.
10A HOUR ON THE OTHER SIDE.
GOOD DAY COMING BACK WITH THE
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
10A HOUR ON THE OTHER SIDE.
♪
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
IT'S LIKE YOGA...
FOR YOUR TASTEBUDS.
OMMMMMMMMMMMMM
NEW TWO GOOD
GREEK LOWFAT YOGURT.
SLOW-STRAINED DOWN
TO 2 GRAMS OF SUGAR.
DO GOOD BY YOU.