DOES YOUR CUSTOMERS
CONNECTING TO THE WIFI
EVER SLOW DOWN YOUR BUSINESS?
YES, IT DOES SLOW THINGS DOWN.
AGGRAVATING.
IT'S A NIGHTMARE.
SO OUR GIG-SPEED
NETWORK IS FAST.
AND WE GO BEYOND FAST BY
MAKING IT EASY TO CREATE
SEPARATE NETWORKS FOR YOUR
BUSINESS AND YOUR CUSTOMERS
AND EVEN CONTROL HOW MUCH
BANDWIDTH EACH OF THOSE GETS.
SO YOUR BUSINESS
WON'T MISS A BEAT.
THIS IS A BIG GAME CHANGER.
THIS IS THE NEW WAVE, AND
WHOEVER DOESN'T GET ON,
I THINK THEY WOULD
BE LEFT BEHIND.
WIFI PRO RUNS ON THE
GIG-SPEED NETWORK.
PAY JUST $49.95 A MONTH
FOR FAST INTERNET
AND GET A $300 PREPAID CARD.
COMCAST BUSINESS.
BEYOND FAST.
Your favorite restaurants now
deliver with DoorDash.
♪
It doesn't matter
where you are.
♪
It doesn't matter what
you're hungry for.
It doesn't even matter
how many you are.
♪
Restaurants come to you.
Delicious at your door.
Download DoorDash.
First order, no delivery fee.
>>> "GOOD MORNING AMERICA" IS
SPONSORED BY STATE FARM'S
NEIGHBORHOOD OF GOOD.
VISIT NEIGHBORHOODOFGOOD.COM TO
VOLUNTEER IN YOUR COMMUNITY.
>>> TIME NOW FOR THE OSCARS'
EDITION OF "POP NEWS."
ADRIENNE, TAKE IT AWAY BECAUSE
I WANT TO EAT THE POPCORN.
>> I LOVE WE HAVE POPCORN FOR
"POP NEWS," BUT AGAIN, EVERYBODY
IS CHECKING OUT THE OSCARS.
>> MM-HMM.
>> NO MATTER THEY WIN OR LOSE,
THE NOMINEES WILL BE BRINGING
HOME SOME OF THIS INSIDE OF
THEIR AMAZING SWAG BAG.
DISTINCTIVE ASSETS WHICH IS AN
INDEPENDENT COMPANY NOT PROVIDED
BY THE ACADEMY PROVIDE THESE TO
THE TOP TALENT.
IN ADDITION TO HEALTH AND BEAUTY
PRODUCTS, THEY HAVE THESE
CANDLES THAT WE HAVE BEEN
SNIFFING ON.
SO YUMMY.
TASTY FOOD, CHOCOLATES OVER
HERE, VACATIONS TO CALIFORNIA,
GREECE ALONG WITH PERSONAL
TRAINING SESSIONS, SPA
EXPERIENCES.
EACH GIFT BAG IS VALUED AT MORE
THAN SIX FIGURES.
DAN IS DROPPING POPCORN.
>> SPILLING ALL OVER HIMSELF.
A PREVIEW OF WHAT HE'LL BE DOING
WITH HIS SWEATPANTS.
>> HE'LL BE WATCHING THE OSCARS
WITH HIS LOVELY WIFE'S
SWEA
SWEATPANTS.
>> THE DRAW STRING.
>> SPEAKING OF FASHION WHEN IT
COMES TO THE OSCAR LOOKS, IT MAY
NOT BE WHO YOU WEAR, BUT WHAT
COLOR.
THE FASHION BRAND ACCESS RISE
ANALYZED OVER 40 YEARS OF
STYLES.
IT TURNS OUT THE
LUCKIEST IS GOLD, WHICH EMMA
STONE WORE WHEN SHE WON FOR "LA
LA LAND."
43% OF NOMINEES WHO WORE GOLD
TOOK HOME THE OSCAR.
THE UNLUCKIEST COLOR IS GREEN
LIKE KATE WINSLET WORE IN 1998.
AGAIN, THAT WAS 1998.
SHE WON AN OSCAR TEN YEARS LATER
WEARING SILVER.
APPARENTLY METALLIC IS A GOOD
THING.
EVERYTHING SHINY.
>> THAT MOVIE IS A GOOD THING,
AND EMMA STONE IS REALLY GREAT
IN IT.
IS SHE NOMINATED?
I CAN'T EVEN REMEMBER.
GO, EMMA.
>> WITHOUT THE OSCARS, YOU
WOULDN'T HAVE THE RAZZIES, WHICH
HONORS LESS SPECTACULAR --
>> WHIT'S FAVORITE MOVIES.
>> EXACTLY.
>> WATCH.
>> BINGE WATCH CLASSICS.
>> THE MOVIE "HOLMES & WATSON"
IS THE BIG WINNER IF YOU WANT TO
CALL IT THAT.
TAKING HOME PRIZES FOR WORST
PICTURE, WORST --
>> I HAVE NOT SEEN THIS ONE, BUT
I MEAN COME ON.
>> WORST SUPPORTING ACTOR FOR
JOHN C. REILLY, AND MELISSA
McCARTHY WAS NAMED WORST ACTRESS
FOR "LIFE OF THE PARTY,"
AND "THE HAPPY TIME MURDERS,"
AND SHE IS UP FOR AN OSCAR
FOR "CAN YOU EVER FOR GIVE ME?"
SHE IS ON BOTH END OF THE
SPE
SPECTRUM.
>> SHOWING RANGE.
>> WE ALL DO.
WE ALL HAVE SOME RANGE.
FINALLY.
EVERYONE WANTS TO DO THEIR OWN
COVER OF "SHALLOW" FROM "A STAR
IS BORN."
YESTERDAY IT WAS NICK JONAS, AND
TODAY IT'S KATE HUDSON BELTING
IT OUT WHILE DOING PILATES.
♪ WATCH AS I DIVE IN ♪
>> WHO KNEW?
>> SHE SOUNDS AMAZING.
>> SHE DOES.
>> KEEP YOUR TAIL DOWN.
>> I'M PULLING MY HAMSTRING JUST
WATCHING THIS.
>> AND SHE'S DOING IT.
FOCUS, HONEY.
CONCENTRATE.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE THE RIGHT FORM
HERE.
>> I NEVER KNEW WHAT PILATES
WAS.
>> IT'S THE REFORMER, RIGHT?
ANYWAYS.
>>> ONE REMINDER, YOU KNOW, WE
HAVE GOT A LOT OF ACTION FOR
YOU, RIGHT?
COMING UP.
>> YOU CAN CATCH THE BIG OSCAR
COUNTDOWN SHOW LIVE FROM THE RED
CARPET STARTING AT 1:00 EASTERN.
>> AND YOU CAN WATCH THE SHOW
ITSELF LIVE AT 8:00 EASTERN.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING THIS
MORNING.
HAVE A GREAT SUNDAY.
>> ENJOY.
BYE.
WATCHING THIS
MORNING.
HAVE A GREAT SUNDAY.
>> ENJOY.
BYE.
>> Meteorologist HELLO AND GOOD
MORNING, WASHINGTON.
CLOUDY SKIES AND THE RAIN IS
TAPERING OFF.
WE'LL SEE CLEARING THIS
AFTERNOON AND GIFT WINDS.
WE HAVE A WEATHER ALERT WITH
HIGH WIND WARNING.
40 DEGREES AND WASHINGTON D.C.
37.
MARTINS BURG ANDLEONARD TOWN.
STILL CHILLY OUT THERE RIGHT
NOW.
BUT MIDDAY, TEMPERATURES SHOULD
BE ADJUST AROUND 50 DEGREES.
SKIES WILL CLEAR IN THE
AFTERNOON AND JUMPING IN THE
MID-60s JUST SHORTLY AND BRIEFLY
AND DIPPING BACK IN THE 50S AND
40s LATER ON TONIGHT.
LOCAL RADAR.
YOU CAN SEE A FEW SHOWERS
LINGERING AT THIS HOUR.
IT WILL BE ALL OUT OF HERE IN
THE NEXT HOUR OR SO.
WIND ADVISORY AND SOUTH AND EAST
IN SOUTHERN MARYLAND.
MORGAN AND BERKELEY AND THEY
COULD HAVE GUSTS TO UP TO 60
MILES PER HOUR.
FUTURE CAST, BY 3:30 THIS
AFTERNOON.
MIDGUST AND 50S TO THE I- 81
CORRIDOR.
THERE IS STRONG WINDS AND WE MAY
SEE A BREAK LATER ON THIS
EVENING AND TONIGHT.
BUT TOMORROW MORNING, MORE GUSTS
IN THE 50S WILL BE POSSIBLE.
THAT'S WHAT WE WILL BE WATCHING
CLOSELY AS WE HAD A INCH OF RAIN
AND SATURATED GROUNDS AND TREES
COULD BE DOWN AND A BIT OF
A COMMUTE PROBLEM EARLY TOMORROW
MORNING AND ADVISORIES AND
WARNINGS EXPIRE AND THAT IS NOT
THE WARMTH WE HAVE TODAY.
LATER ON THIS WEEK.
DRY IN THE MID TO UPPER 40s AND