AND THE RESTLESS IS FOUND DEAD.
>> DON'T MISS PART TWO OF
KEVIN'S INTERVIEW WITH SUPER
STAR CHRIS PRATT.
THEY ARE TALKING ALL ABOUT THE
NEW LEGO MOVIE.
PLUS HE WAS A GAY TAR RIFT FOR
ALICIA, AND NOW HE HAS A NEW
SINGLE OF IT.
CRAIG STICK LAND IS HERE AND
WILL PERFORM IT LIVE RIGHT HERE
IN THE LOFT.
>> LET'S DO THIS IN THREE, TWO,
ONE.
THE 10A STARTS NOW.
>> ♪
>> IT'S ALMOST VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> I KNOW.
>> I GOT YOU SOMETHING.
>> LOOK AT YOU.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE, ROSE PETALS.
>> ROSE PETALS.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT MAKES IT EVEN
BETTER.
>> WHAT'S THAT.
>> PUT THIS IN CHOCOLATE.
>> CAN WE DO THAT.
>> YES, YOU CAN.
CHECK IT OUT RIGHT HERE THE GUYS
FROM, THEY'LL EXPLAIN THAT WHAT
MEANS.
THEY'LL TEACH US HOW TO MAKE
TRUFFLES.
YOU'LL TELL US ABOUT THE
CRAFTING.
>> WE CAN LEARNED TO THIS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> I LIKE THE AFTER.
I CAN'T WAIT I SEE THE BEFORE.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THE DURING
MUCH THIS WILL BE FUN.
>> THERE'S A SCIENCE THAT GOES
INTO THIS WHICH ERICA WILL TELL
US ALL ABOUT IT.
THE PROCESS.
YOU'LL SEE WHY IT'S SUCH A GOOD
PROCESS AND WHY IT'S SO
DELICIOUS.
WE'LL LEARN ALL ABOUT THAT.
AROUND 10:40.
>> LET YOU GUYS GET READY.
>> VERY COOL.
>> ALL THE HIGH TECH EQUIPMENT.
>> THIS IS CHRIS.
SHE'S THE ONE WHO MAKES IT.
SHE'S THE SILENT ONE WHO DOES
ALL THE WORK.
WE'RE COMING BACK TO TALK TO ALL
OF THEM IN JUST A BIT.
>> AWESOME.
GOOD DAY AT 10A STARTING RIGHT
NOW.
>>> ♪
>>> I LOVE IT.
>> I MIGHT HAVE TO TRY ONE OR
TWO OR FIVE.
>> EXACTLY.
>> BOXES?
>> A BOX.
WHY NOT?
>> 10:01 RIGHT NOW.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>>> THANKS FOR STICKING AROUND
FOR THE 10A TODAY.
IT SHOULD BE A GOOD HOUR.
FIRST AT 10:00, THOUGH WE HAVE
TO TALK ABOUT THE BIG STORY
THAT'S HAPPENING IN VIRGINIA
RIGHT NOW.
RALPH NORTHAM'S FUTURE IN
RICHMOND THE GOVERNOR HOLDING
URGENT LATE NIGHT MEETING WITH
HIS INNER CIRCLE SUNDAY AS HE
FACES THE ON-GOING FALLOUT FROM
THAT RACIST YEARBOOK PICTURE.
>> DEMOCRAT MAINTAINS HE WAS NOT
IN THE PICTURE WHICH SHOWS ONE
PERSON IN BLACK FACE AND ANOTHER
IN A KKK ROBE.
BUT OVER THE WEEKEND, HE AD
ADMITTED HE HAD WORN LACTATION
BEFORE AND DESPITE REPEATED
CALLS FOR HESS RESIGNATION FROM
STATE AND NATIONAL LEADERS ON
BOTH SIDES OF THE AISLE, HE HAS
SHOWN NO SIGNS OF BACKING DOWN.
>> FOR MORE ON THE FALLOUT AND
WHAT COULD COME NEXT, OUR CORI
COFFIN, SHE IS LIVE OUTSIDE THE
GOVERNOR'S MANSION IN RICHMOND
WITH THE VERY LATEST.
GOOD MORNING.
CORI.
>> Reporter: GOOD MORNING, TO
ALL OF YOU.
ALL EYES WILL BE ON THE
GOVERNOR'S MANSION THIS MORNING
AS HE HAD THAT LATE NIGHT
MEETING.
WE'RE UNDERSTANDING THAT THIS
ALSO INVOLVED THE INNER CIRCLE
OF THIS CORE TEAM AND WE DON'T
KNOW YET WHAT EXACTLY WAS THE
OUT COME OF THAT MEETING BUT
MORE PEOPLE WILL BEGIN TO ARRIVE
HERE AT THE MANSION, AND OUTSIDE
HERE AT THE STATE HOUSE PROMPT
IN GENERAL.
THERE'S SOME PROTESTER WHO'S
HAVE NOW ARRIVED.
THEY TELL ME THAT THEY PLAN ON
GATHERING STARTING HERE IN JUST
THE NEXT FEW MINUTES.
YOU CAN SEE MEDIA STARTING TO
PICK UP AS WELL.
WE'VE SEEN SOME SIGNS CALLING ON
NORTHAM'S RESIGNATION.
SOME FOLKS GIVING INTERVIEWS,
DEFINITELY A LOT MORE HAPPENING
THIS MORNING AS THE SUN HAS COME
UP AND THE DAY HAS BEGUN.
NOW, AS THESE PROTESTERS HAVE
BEGUN ARRIVING HERE ON THE
GROUNDS WE ALSO KNOW THAT RIGHT
HERE NEXT STORE TO THE MANSION
SPEAKER OF THE HOUSE HAS ALSO
GIVEN HIS OWN FORMAL STATEMENT
CALLING FOR NORTHAM'S
RESIGNATION.
OF COURSE, AS YOU KNOW, THIS ALL
STEMS FROM THAT PHOTO THAT CAME
TO LIGHT ON FRIDAY THAT APPEARED
TO SHOW IN THE MEDICAL SCHOOL
YEARBOOK ON RALPH NORTHAM'S
SENIOR PAGE IT APPEARED TO SHOW
A PICTURE OF SOMEBODY WITH BLACK
FACE AS WELL AS SOMEONE ELSE
STANDING NEXT TO THEM WITH KKK
GARB.
NOW, FIRST NORTHAM SAID HE WOULD
TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE
PHOTO AND HE APOLOGIZED.
HE THEN SAID IT WAS NOT HIM IN
THE PHOTO AS OF THIS POINT HE IS
REMAINING IN OFFICE BUT, OF
COURSE, AS WE KNOW THAT REMAINS
TO BE SEEN AS MORE PEOPLE CALL
FOR HIM TO STEP DOWN.
THE OFFICIAL DEMOCRATIC PARTY
HERE THE STATE OF VIRGINIA IS
ALSO BACKING LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR
JUSTIN FAIRFAX FOR -- TO STEP
INTO THAT ROLE.
SO WE'LL KEEP YOU APPRISED OF
WHAT HAPPENS HERE IN RICHMOND AS
ALL OF THIS ACTIVITY STARTS TO
KICK UP.
BUT FOR NOW WE'LL SEND IT BACK
TO YOU IN THE GUYS IN THE
STUDIO.
>> CORI COFFIN THANK YOU FOR
THAT UPDATE.
TIME RIGHT NOW ZEN 03:00.
>>> LET'S CHECK WHAT IS TRENDING
THIS MORNING.
>> FIRST UP LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
SUPER BOWL.
SUPER BOWL LIII BECAUSE LOVE HIM
OR HATE HIM TOM BRADY CONTINUE
TO GO SILENT THE CRITICS AND
PROVE HE MAY BE THE GREATEST
QUARTERBACK OF ALL TIME.
IT WAS AN UGLY GAME.
BUT WHEN IT WAS OVER THE
41-YEAR-OLD PATRIOTS STAR WAS
ONCE AGAIN SUPER BOWL CHAMPION.
THIS IS HIS RECORD SETTING SIXTH
SUPER BOWL WIN AND HE'S NOT DONE
YET BECAUSE HE SAYS HE STILL
WANTS TO PLAY AND HE WANTS TO
KEEP GOING UNTIL HE'S 45 YEARS
OLD.
>> GOOD FOR HIM.
>> WHY NOT?
I CAN COME TO GRIPS.
>> GOOD FOR HIM.
I'M NOT A PATRIOTS FAN OR TOM
I CAN COME TO GRIPS.
BRADY FAN I GET TIRED OF THE
I'M NOT A PATRIOTS FAN OR TOM
SAME TEAM WINNING ALL THE TIME.
BRADY FAN I GET TIRED OF THE
>> UM-HMM.
SAME TEAM WINNING ALL THE TIME.
>> I CAN COME TO GRIPS, YES, I
>> UM-HMM.
BELIEVE TOM BRADY IS THE
>> I CAN COME TO GRIPS, YES, I
GREATEST QUARTERBACK OF ALL T
BELIEVE TOM BRADY IS THE
TIME.
GREATEST QUARTERBACK OF ALL T
I DON'T THINK YOU CAN DISPUTE
TIME.
THAT UNLESS YOU'RE WIS TOM
I DON'T THINK YOU CAN DISPUTE
MARTIN.
THAT UNLESS YOU'RE WIS TOM
>> HE IS THE GREATEST AFTER JOE
MARTIN.
MONTANA.
>> HE IS THE GREATEST AFTER JOE
I CAN ROLL WITH YOU ON THAT.
MONTANA.
>> WHY?
I CAN ROLL WITH YOU ON THAT.
>> WHY DO YOU THINK JOE MONTANA.
>> WHY?
>> FOUR-ZERO IN THE SUPER BOWL.
>> WHY DO YOU THINK JOE MONTANA.
NEVER LOST.
>> FOUR-ZERO IN THE SUPER BOWL.
NEVER THROUGH AN INTERCEPTION IN
NEVER LOST.
FOUR GAMES.
NEVER THROUGH AN INTERCEPTION IN
DO YOU KNOW HOW HARD THAT IS TO
FOUR GAMES.
PLAY IN FOUR OF THE BIGGEST
DO YOU KNOW HOW HARD THAT IS TO
GAMES OF YOUR CAREER AND NOT
PLAY IN FOUR OF THE BIGGEST
THROW A INTERCEPTION AND WIN ALL
GAMES OF YOUR CAREER AND NOT
FOUR OF THEM.
THROW A INTERCEPTION AND WIN ALL
>> WOULD YOU PUT BRADY NUMBER
FOUR OF THEM.
TWO?
>> WOULD YOU PUT BRADY NUMBER
>> HE CAN BE NUMBER TWO.
TWO?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> HE CAN BE NUMBER TWO.
>> WHO ELSE WOULD BE NUMBER TWO?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> NO, NO, BRADY IS NUMBER TWO.
>> WHO ELSE WOULD BE NUMBER TWO?
>> YOU THINK HE'S TWO.
>> NO, NO, BRADY IS NUMBER TWO.
>> HE CAN BE NUMBER TWO.
>> YOU THINK HE'S TWO.
>> IS THREE WAY DOWN HERE OR --
>> HE CAN BE NUMBER TWO.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO NUMBER THREE
>> IS THREE WAY DOWN HERE OR --
IS.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO NUMBER THREE
>> THERE YOU GO.
IS.
>> ONE AND TWO YOU'RE DONE.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> WHAT WASN'T NUMBER ONE OR
>> ONE AND TWO YOU'RE DONE.
TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE, SIX,
>> WHAT WASN'T NUMBER ONE OR
SEVEN, EIGHT OR NINE?
TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE, SIX,
>> WHAT'S THAT?
SEVEN, EIGHT OR NINE?
>> THE SUPER BOWL RATINGS.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> OH YEAH.
>> THE SUPER BOWL RATINGS.
>> LOWEST RATES IN TEN YEARS.
>> OH YEAH.
>> I'M NOT SURPRISED.
>> LOWEST RATES IN TEN YEARS.
>> I'M WONDERING ALSO WHAT
>> I'M NOT SURPRISED.
PEOPLE WERE WATCHING INSTEAD OR
>> I'M WONDERING ALSO WHAT
WERE THEY JUST NOT WATCHING TV
PEOPLE WERE WATCHING INSTEAD OR
AT ALL.
WERE THEY JUST NOT WATCHING TV
>> I THINK JUST TURNING IT OFF.
AT ALL.
>> TURNING IT OFF.
>> I THINK JUST TURNING IT OFF.
BECAUSE WE TALKED ABOUT THIS.
>> TURNING IT OFF.
I STRUGGLED TO CONTINUE TO WATCH
BECAUSE WE TALKED ABOUT THIS.
AT ONE POINT.
I STRUGGLED TO CONTINUE TO WATCH
>> ME TOO.
AT ONE POINT.
>> I FELT LIKE I HAD TO WATCH
>> ME TOO.
FOR WORK.
>> I FELT LIKE I HAD TO WATCH
>> I NEVER TURNED OFF A SUPER
FOR WORK.
BOWL.
>> I NEVER TURNED OFF A SUPER
TUCKER SAID THIS MORNING HE
BOWL.
FOUND HIM ITSELF DISTRACTED IN
TUCKER SAID THIS MORNING HE
THE SECOND HALF AND WAS DOING
FOUND HIM ITSELF DISTRACTED IN
OTHER THINGS EVEN THOUGH THE
THE SECOND HALF AND WAS DOING
GAME WAS STILL ON I'M SURE
OTHER THINGS EVEN THOUGH THE
THERE'S SOME PEOPLE WHO LIKE,
GAME WAS STILL ON I'M SURE
OKAY, I'M JUST TURNING IT OFF.
THERE'S SOME PEOPLE WHO LIKE,
>> MULTIPLE PROBLEMS WITH THE
OKAY, I'M JUST TURNING IT OFF.
GAME THE FACT THAT YOU MENTIONED
>> MULTIPLE PROBLEMS WITH THE
THAT THE PATRIOTS ARE IN IT
GAME THE FACT THAT YOU MENTIONED
EVERY SINGLE YEAR.
THAT THE PATRIOTS ARE IN IT
I THINK THERE'S -- OUTSIDE OF
EVERY SINGLE YEAR.
BOSTON AND THE BOSTON CROWD AND
I THINK THERE'S -- OUTSIDE OF
THE PATRIOTS LOVERS I THINK
BOSTON AND THE BOSTON CROWD AND
THERE'S PATRIOTS FATIGUE.
THE PATRIOTS LOVERS I THINK
PEOPLE ARE TIRED OF THAT, AND
THERE'S PATRIOTS FATIGUE.
THEN YOU FACTOR IN LA, I THINK
PEOPLE ARE TIRED OF THAT, AND
THAT NFL IS MISGUIDED WITH THIS
THEN YOU FACTOR IN LA, I THINK
WHOLE LOS ANGELES THING.
THAT NFL IS MISGUIDED WITH THIS
THEY THINK THAT BECAUSE IT'S THE
WHOLE LOS ANGELES THING.
NUMBER TWO MARK IN THE COUNTRY
THEY THINK THAT BECAUSE IT'S THE
THAT PEOPLE ARE, OOH, LA.
NUMBER TWO MARK IN THE COUNTRY
PEOPLE IN LA DON'T GIVE A FLIP
THAT PEOPLE ARE, OOH, LA.
ABOUT THE RAMS.
PEOPLE IN LA DON'T GIVE A FLIP
I'M SORRY, THEY DON'T.
ABOUT THE RAMS.
>> THEY DON'T CARE ABOUT THE
I'M SORRY, THEY DON'T.
RAMS.
>> THEY DON'T CARE ABOUT THE
>> EXCEPT WHEN THEY WIN.
RAMS.
>> UNTIL THEY WIN.
>> EXCEPT WHEN THEY WIN.
THE WHOLE WEST COAST EAST COAST.
>> UNTIL THEY WIN.
THERE IS NO -- THERE'S NO FAN
THE WHOLE WEST COAST EAST COAST.
BASE.
THERE IS NO -- THERE'S NO FAN
NO HARD-CORE FAN BASE IN LOS
BASE.
ANGELES THAT'S GO TO FOLLOW THE
NO HARD-CORE FAN BASE IN LOS
RAMS ALL OVER THE COUNTRY.
ANGELES THAT'S GO TO FOLLOW THE
THEY JUST DO NOT EXIST.
RAMS ALL OVER THE COUNTRY.
THAT'S WHY THEY LEFT IN THE
THEY JUST DO NOT EXIST.
FIRST PLACE 20 SOMETHING YEARS
THAT'S WHY THEY LEFT IN THE
AGO.
FIRST PLACE 20 SOMETHING YEARS
>> FROM MY PERSPECTIVE I JUST
AGO.
FEEL LIKE FOOTBALL IS NOT WHAT
>> FROM MY PERSPECTIVE I JUST
IT USED TO BE.
FEEL LIKE FOOTBALL IS NOT WHAT
>> THERE'S THAT, TOO.
IT USED TO BE.
>> OVERALL DON'T CARE LIKE THEY
>> THERE'S THAT, TOO.
USED TOM THE RIVALRIES AREN'T AS
>> OVERALL DON'T CARE LIKE THEY
EXCITING AS THEY USED TO BE.
USED TOM THE RIVALRIES AREN'T AS
>> THE WHOLE CONCUSSION ISSUE.
EXCITING AS THEY USED TO BE.
>> A BUNCH OF ISSUES NOW THAT
>> THE WHOLE CONCUSSION ISSUE.
HAVE JUST MARRED THE GAME AS A
>> A BUNCH OF ISSUES NOW THAT
WHOLE.
HAVE JUST MARRED THE GAME AS A
>> COLIN KAEPERNICK THING LOTS
WHOLE.
OF PEOPLE DIDN'T WATCH BECAUSE
>> COLIN KAEPERNICK THING LOTS
OF THAT.
OF PEOPLE DIDN'T WATCH BECAUSE
>> THE TIME.
OF THAT.
>> PEOPLE IN NEW ORLEANS DIDN'T
>> THE TIME.
WATCH BECAUSE -- ANYBODY THAT
>> PEOPLE IN NEW ORLEANS DIDN'T
WAS NFL FAN THOUGHT THAT THE
WATCH BECAUSE -- ANYBODY THAT
SAINTS SHOULD HAVE BEEN THERE
WAS NFL FAN THOUGHT THAT THE
INSTEAD OF THE RAMS WERE DISS
SAINTS SHOULD HAVE BEEN THERE
ENCHANTED SO THERE WERE A LOT OF
INSTEAD OF THE RAMS WERE DISS
THINGS GOING ON.
ENCHANTED SO THERE WERE A LOT OF
>> BIGGEST SPORTS FAN IN THE
THINGS GOING ON.
WORLD DID YOU WATCH ANY OF IT
>> BIGGEST SPORTS FAN IN THE
YESTERDAY.
WORLD DID YOU WATCH ANY OF IT
>> I DIDN'T WATCH AT ALL.
YESTERDAY.
I WASN'T GOING TO.
>> I DIDN'T WATCH AT ALL.
DESPITE THE FACT I'M NOT A FAN,
I WASN'T GOING TO.
I WAS TAKING A STAND ABOUT THE
DESPITE THE FACT I'M NOT A FAN,
NFL IN GENERAL I WAS NOT GOING
I WAS TAKING A STAND ABOUT THE
TO WATCH.
NFL IN GENERAL I WAS NOT GOING
DIDN'T CARE.
TO WATCH.
STARTED LATE ANY WAY.
DIDN'T CARE.
6:00 O'CLOCK TO ME IS -- COME ON
STARTED LATE ANY WAY.
ESPECIALLY ON SUNDAY NIGHT.
6:00 O'CLOCK TO ME IS -- COME ON
>> IN FAIRNESS IT STARTS THE
ESPECIALLY ON SUNDAY NIGHT.
SAME TIME EVERY YEAR.
>> IN FAIRNESS IT STARTS THE
>> IT DOES.
SAME TIME EVERY YEAR.
IT'S NOT INTERESTING ME.
>> IT DOES.
FOOTBALL AS A WHOLE IS NOT
IT'S NOT INTERESTING ME.
INTERESTING TO ME AS AN ADULT.
FOOTBALL AS A WHOLE IS NOT
NOW EVEN BASKETBALL WHICH I
INTERESTING TO ME AS AN ADULT.
LOVE, EVEN THAT'S NOT AS
NOW EVEN BASKETBALL WHICH I
EXCITING I JUST DON'T THINK THE
LOVE, EVEN THAT'S NOT AS
SPORTS IS WHAT USED TO BE.
EXCITING I JUST DON'T THINK THE
THERE'S TOO MUCH COME INTO PLAY
SPORTS IS WHAT USED TO BE.
IN RECENT YEARS THAT IT'S NOT
THERE'S TOO MUCH COME INTO PLAY
FUN FOR ME.
IN RECENT YEARS THAT IT'S NOT
NOW, YOU KNOW, PEOPLE HAVE THEIR
FUN FOR ME.
OWN OPINION.
NOW, YOU KNOW, PEOPLE HAVE THEIR
THAT'S FINE.
OWN OPINION.
FOR ME, EH I COULD LEAVE IT.
THAT'S FINE.
>> MILLIONS AND MILLIONS OF
FOR ME, EH I COULD LEAVE IT.
PEOPLE WATCHING.
>> MILLIONS AND MILLIONS OF
WHEN YOU PUT IT UP AGAINST THE
PEOPLE WATCHING.
LAST TEN, THIS ONE DIDN'T MAKE
WHEN YOU PUT IT UP AGAINST THE
THE CUT.
LAST TEN, THIS ONE DIDN'T MAKE
>> WELL, AS IF THE FOOTBALL GAME
THE CUT.
WASN'T DISAPPOINTING ENOUGH, HOW
>> WELL, AS IF THE FOOTBALL GAME
ABOUT THAT DISAPPOINTING SUPER
WASN'T DISAPPOINTING ENOUGH, HOW
BOWL HALF TIME SHOW?  MAROON
ABOUT THAT DISAPPOINTING SUPER
FIVE STARTED OFF THEIR HALF TIME
BOWL HALF TIME SHOW?  MAROON
SHOW PERFORMANCE WITH SONGS OFF
FIVE STARTED OFF THEIR HALF TIME
THEIR DEBUT ALBUM.
SHOW PERFORMANCE WITH SONGS OFF
SONGS ABOUT JANE ADAM LEVINE
THEIR DEBUT ALBUM.
STROLLED ON STAGE AND INDUSTRIAL
SONGS ABOUT JANE ADAM LEVINE
GOOD WORK AND LAUNCHED INTO
STROLLED ON STAGE AND INDUSTRIAL
HARDER TO BREATHE AND THIS LOVE
GOOD WORK AND LAUNCHED INTO
BOTH HITS FROM THE BAND'S 2002
HARDER TO BREATHE AND THIS LOVE
RELEASE.
BOTH HITS FROM THE BAND'S 2002
MAROON FIVE ENDED ON A VERY
RELEASE.
PREDICTABLE NOTE HE TOOK OFF HIS
MAROON FIVE ENDED ON A VERY
SHIRT TO SING THE 2007 HIT MOVES
PREDICTABLE NOTE HE TOOK OFF HIS
LIKE JAGGER.
SHIRT TO SING THE 2007 HIT MOVES
HE GOT BACKLASH ON THAT THOUGH.
LIKE JAGGER.
NOT CRITICS CALLING IT A DOUBLE
HE GOT BACKLASH ON THAT THOUGH.
STANDARD AFTER SHOWING NIPPLE
NOT CRITICS CALLING IT A DOUBLE
NEARLY ENDED JANET JACKSON'S
STANDARD AFTER SHOWING NIPPLE
CAREER.
NEARLY ENDED JANET JACKSON'S
MEANWHILE SOME COULDN'T BELIEVE
CAREER.
IT FEATURED A SPONGE BOB SQUARE
MEANWHILE SOME COULDN'T BELIEVE
PANTS TRIBUTE.
IT FEATURED A SPONGE BOB SQUARE
HALF TIME SHOW CUT TO A CLIP
PANTS TRIBUTE.
FROM THE AN 98ED SERIES FAMOUS
HALF TIME SHOW CUT TO A CLIP
BAND GEEK EPISODE TO INTRODUCE
FROM THE AN 98ED SERIES FAMOUS
TRAVIS SCOTT.
BAND GEEK EPISODE TO INTRODUCE
YOU SEE THERE.
TRAVIS SCOTT.
THE MOVE CAME AFTER SPONGE BOB
YOU SEE THERE.
FANS PETITIONED FOR THE CLIP TO
THE MOVE CAME AFTER SPONGE BOB
APPEAR DURING THE CHAMPIONSHIP
FANS PETITIONED FOR THE CLIP TO
SINCE THE SHOW'S CREATOR STEVEN
APPEAR DURING THE CHAMPIONSHIP
HILL BURG DIED IN SEPTEMBER.
SINCE THE SHOW'S CREATOR STEVEN
>> BIG BOY JOINED THE STAGE WAY
HILL BURG DIED IN SEPTEMBER.
MAROON FIVE.
>> BIG BOY JOINED THE STAGE WAY
HE SANG THE WAY YOU MOVE.
MAROON FIVE.
THE ONLY SUPER BOWL MUSIC
HE SANG THE WAY YOU MOVE.
GETTING HIGH MARK THIS MORNING
THE ONLY SUPER BOWL MUSIC
YOU HEARD A LITTLE BIT OF IT
GETTING HIGH MARK THIS MORNING
THERE WAS GLADYS KNIGHT.
YOU HEARD A LITTLE BIT OF IT
THERE SHE IS.
THERE WAS GLADYS KNIGHT.
HER RENDITION OF THE NATIONAL
THERE SHE IS.
ANTHEM THE ATLANTA NATIVE WORE A
HER RENDITION OF THE NATIONAL
WHITE DRESS AND SILVER BOOTIES
ANTHEM THE ATLANTA NATIVE WORE A
WE EMBELLISHED HEAD BAND.
WHITE DRESS AND SILVER BOOTIES
SHE HIT THE FINAL NOTE FIEF 16S
WE EMBELLISHED HEAD BAND.
THROUGH OVER THE STADIUM IN
SHE HIT THE FINAL NOTE FIEF 16S
FORMATION.
THROUGH OVER THE STADIUM IN
IT WAS A HUGE HIT ON SOCIAL
FORMATION.
MEDIA.
IT WAS A HUGE HIT ON SOCIAL
MANY WERE PRAISING I'M CONNICK
MEDIA.
SINGER.
MANY WERE PRAISING I'M CONNICK
>> GLADYS NIGHT A DID FANTASTIC
SINGER.
JOB.
>> GLADYS NIGHT A DID FANTASTIC
SHE WENT OVER THE TWO MINUTES 46
JOB.
SECONDS WHICH WAS THE PROP BET.
SHE WENT OVER THE TWO MINUTES 46
AS FAR AS MAROON FIVE AND THE
SECONDS WHICH WAS THE PROP BET.
HALF TIME SHOW YOU GOT WHAT YOU
AS FAR AS MAROON FIVE AND THE
EXPECTED.
HALF TIME SHOW YOU GOT WHAT YOU
>> RIGHT.
EXPECTED.
>> I DON'T THINK ANYBODY HAD
>> RIGHT.
HUGE EXPECTATIONS FOR THIS.
>> I DON'T THINK ANYBODY HAD
I THINK THAT IF THE BAND WANTED
HUGE EXPECTATIONS FOR THIS.
TO LADY GAGA COME DOWN FROM THE
I THINK THAT IF THE BAND WANTED
RAFTERS HAVE A GRAND OPENING
TO LADY GAGA COME DOWN FROM THE
THAT WOULD HAVE ELEVATED THINGS.
RAFTERS HAVE A GRAND OPENING
THAT'S NOT WHAT THIS BAND IS.
THAT WOULD HAVE ELEVATED THINGS.
THEY DO WHAT THEY DID.
THAT'S NOT WHAT THIS BAND IS.
>> THE FIRE AT THE END.
THEY DO WHAT THEY DID.
>> WHEN DID THE HALF TIME SHOW
>> THE FIRE AT THE END.
BECOME A THING FOR THE -- FOR
>> WHEN DID THE HALF TIME SHOW
THE SUPER BOWLS?  I FEEL LIKE
BECOME A THING FOR THE -- FOR
NOW IT'S BECOME SO IMPORTANT
THE SUPER BOWLS?  I FEEL LIKE
THEY HAVE A GREAT PERFORMER THAT
NOW IT'S BECOME SO IMPORTANT
ALMOST ECLIPSES THE GAME SOME IN
THEY HAVE A GREAT PERFORMER THAT
SOME WAYS.
ALMOST ECLIPSES THE GAME SOME IN
WHEN DID IT BECOME IF YOU DON'T
SOME WAYS.
HAVE THIS GREAT PERFORMER --
WHEN DID IT BECOME IF YOU DON'T
>> THE IDEA WAS FOR THE CASUAL
HAVE THIS GREAT PERFORMER --
FAN.
>> THE IDEA WAS FOR THE CASUAL
>> IT STARTED BACK IN WHATEVER
FAN.
YEAR THAT WAS.
>> IT STARTED BACK IN WHATEVER
'90 SOMETHING.
YEAR THAT WAS.
>> IT'S GOT TO FEVER PITCH YOU
'90 SOMETHING.
GET MAROON FIVE WHICH IS A
>> IT'S GOT TO FEVER PITCH YOU
GREAT, GREAT BAND BUT NOW
GET MAROON FIVE WHICH IS A
THEREAT GOODING SO MUCH FLACK
GREAT, GREAT BAND BUT NOW
FOR NOT PERFORMING UP TO THE
THEREAT GOODING SO MUCH FLACK
STANDARDS OF A SUPER BOWL HALF
FOR NOT PERFORMING UP TO THE
TIME SHOW I DON'T THINK IS
STANDARDS OF A SUPER BOWL HALF
NECESSARILY FAIR.
TIME SHOW I DON'T THINK IS
>> THE BEST PART WAS BIG BOY'S
NECESSARILY FAIR.
ENTRANCE.
>> THE BEST PART WAS BIG BOY'S
>> THAT WAS PRETTY COOL.
ENTRANCE.
>> I DID LIKE THAT.
>> THAT WAS PRETTY COOL.
>> I LIKE THE DRUM LINE I WILL
>> I DID LIKE THAT.
SAY.
>> I LIKE THE DRUM LINE I WILL
>> THE DRUM LINE WAS GOOD.
SAY.
THE CHOIR WAS GOOD.
>> THE DRUM LINE WAS GOOD.
BUT I AGREE WITH KEVIN MCCARTHY
THE CHOIR WAS GOOD.
A HUNDRED PERCENT WE KNOW WE
BUT I AGREE WITH KEVIN MCCARTHY
DON'T ALWAYS AGREE WITH KEVIN.
A HUNDRED PERCENT WE KNOW WE
TRAVIS SCOTT DO NOT GIVE -- WHEN
DON'T ALWAYS AGREE WITH KEVIN.
HE'S CURSING.
TRAVIS SCOTT DO NOT GIVE -- WHEN
>> RIGHT.
HE'S CURSING.
>> THEY HAD TO GO TO SILENCE.
>> RIGHT.
IT'S JUST LIKE --
>> THEY HAD TO GO TO SILENCE.
>> SEEMS LIKE THERE'S A MISSION
IT'S JUST LIKE --
HAPPEN WHEN THAT HAMS.
>> SEEMS LIKE THERE'S A MISSION
>> RIGHT.
HAPPEN WHEN THAT HAMS.
>> THE TV GOES SILENT FOR
>> RIGHT.
EXTENDED PERIODS.
>> THE TV GOES SILENT FOR
FOR LIKE ONE PERFORMANCE JUST DO
EXTENDED PERIODS.
IT UP.
FOR LIKE ONE PERFORMANCE JUST DO
>> I ACTUALLY THOUGHT THE
IT UP.
PYROTECHNICS WERE A LITTLE TOO
>> I ACTUALLY THOUGHT THE
MUCH OVER THE TOP.
PYROTECHNICS WERE A LITTLE TOO
I FELT LIKE -- I LITERALLY
MUCH OVER THE TOP.
FOUGHT THE STADIUM WAS GOING TO
I FELT LIKE -- I LITERALLY
EXPLODE IN THE END THERE WAS SO
FOUGHT THE STADIUM WAS GOING TO
MUCH GOING ON IN THE END.
EXPLODE IN THE END THERE WAS SO
>> TRAVIS AND BIG BOY EACH DID
MUCH GOING ON IN THE END.
JUST ONE SONG.
>> TRAVIS AND BIG BOY EACH DID
>> UM-HMM.
JUST ONE SONG.
>> MARINE POOF -- MAROON FIVE
>> UM-HMM.
JOINED BIG BOY FOR A LITTLE BIT
>> MARINE POOF -- MAROON FIVE
THEY PLAYED IN THE BACK.
JOINED BIG BOY FOR A LITTLE BIT
IT WAS MAROON FIVE'S SHOW WITH
THEY PLAYED IN THE BACK.
SPECIAL GUESTS.
IT WAS MAROON FIVE'S SHOW WITH
THAT'S TYPICALLY WHAT THEY DID.
SPECIAL GUESTS.
>> I LIKE ADAM LEVINE BUT I FELL
THAT'S TYPICALLY WHAT THEY DID.
LIKE HE WAS JUST MAILING IT IN.
>> I LIKE ADAM LEVINE BUT I FELL
JUST KIND OF HOPPING AROUND.
LIKE HE WAS JUST MAILING IT IN.
>> SAME TONE AS THE GAME AND THE
JUST KIND OF HOPPING AROUND.
COMMERCIALS.
>> SAME TONE AS THE GAME AND THE
EXACTLY.
COMMERCIALS.
>> YEAH.
EXACTLY.
>> OKAY.
>> YEAH.
>>> 10:11 IS THE TIME.
>> OKAY.
CHRIS PRATT, ELIZABETH BANKS
>>> 10:11 IS THE TIME.
RETURN TO THE LEGO UNIVERSE WITH
CHRIS PRATT, ELIZABETH BANKS
NEW SEQUEL TO THE HEY GO MOVIE
RETURN TO THE LEGO UNIVERSE WITH
CALLED THE SECOND PART.
NEW SEQUEL TO THE HEY GO MOVIE
COMING UP, A LITTLE LATER --
CALLED THE SECOND PART.
>> I KNOW.
COMING UP, A LITTLE LATER --
ROOM FULL OF PEOPLE.
>> I KNOW.
KEVIN SITTING DOWN WITH THE
ROOM FULL OF PEOPLE.
STARS TO LEARN THE SECRET TO
KEVIN SITTING DOWN WITH THE
BROODING ON CAMERA.
STARS TO LEARN THE SECRET TO
>> FIRST THOUGH 21 SAVAGE FACING
BROODING ON CAMERA.
DEPORTATION?  PETE DAVIDSON
>> FIRST THOUGH 21 SAVAGE FACING
MAKING IT OFFICIAL, AND KYLIE
DEPORTATION?  PETE DAVIDSON
AND TRAVIS ADDING TO THE FAMILY
MAKING IT OFFICIAL, AND KYLIE
LOTS OF QUESTIONS.
AND TRAVIS ADDING TO THE FAMILY
HOPEFULLY WE'LL ANSWER THEM ALL
LOTS OF QUESTIONS.
IN THE GOOD DAY CELEBRITY DISH.
HOPEFULLY WE'LL ANSWER THEM ALL
IT'S NEXT.
IN THE GOOD DAY CELEBRITY DISH.
♪
New Vaseline Clinical Care...
...heals extremely dry skin in
just 5 days.
♪ ♪
It's amazing what healed skin
can do.
The healing power of Vaseline.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
Here is another Laundry Hack
from Home Made Simple.
Do you want ready to wear
clothing without all the hassle?
You can, with Bounce Dryer
sheets.
Simply toss two sheets in the
dryer to iron less.
We dried one shirt without
Bounce,
and an identical shirt using
Bounce.
The Bounce shirt has fewer
wrinkles, less static,
and more softness and
freshness.
For extra large or wrinkly
loads, toss in three sheets.
Dermatologist tested Bounce Free
and Gentle
is free of dyes and perfumes.
Bounce out wrinkles, Bounce out
static.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
This is Charlie not coughing
because he took Delsym 12-hour.
And this is Charlie still not
coughing
while trying his hardest not to
wake Zeus.
Delsym 12-hour.
Nothing lasts
longer for powerful
cough relief.
♪
>>> 10:14 IS THE TIME.
LET'S CHECK THE GOOD DAY MEMBER
BEFORE THE DISH.
>> WE'LL START I WAS WITH VERY
SAD NEWS FROM HOLLYWOOD.
TMZ IS REPORTING YOUNG AND
RESTLESS STAR KRISTOFF ST. JOHN
WAS FOUND DEAD.
POLICE SAY THEY FOUND HIM DEAD
AFTER FRIENDS ASKED AUTHORITIES
TO CHECK ON HIM AT HIS SAN
FERNANDO VALLEY HOE.
TMMZ TOLD THERE'S NO SIGN OF
FOUL PLAY.
HE PLAYED THE POPULAR ROLE OF
NEAL WINTERS ON THE YOUNG AND
RESTLESS SINCE 1991.
HE'S BEEN NOMINATED FOR NINE
DAYTIME EMMY AWARDS AND HAS WON
TEN NAACP IMAGE AWARDS.
ST. JOHN ALSO HAD TV ROLLS IN
HANGING WITH MR. COOPER, MARTIN
AND THE BAD NEWS BEARS.
>> ALSO IN ROOTS.
>> UM-HMM.
>> HE WAS THE YOUNG ALEX HALEY.
>> YEAH.
>> AND ALSO IN THIS IS BACK --
THIS IS OBSCURE FACT BECAUSE
THIS WAS BACK IN THE '80S.
FLIP WILSON HAD A FAMILY SHOW.
HE WAS THE KID ON THERE WITH
GLADYS KNIGHT ON THE SHOW ON
THAT SHOW.
>> I THINK HE WAS ALSO IN A SOAP
OPERA CALLED GENERATIONS ONE OF
THE FIRST LIKE --
>> I THINK SO.
>> NOT THE FIRST
AFRICAN-AMERICAN SOAP OPERA THE
WHOLE FAMILY.
I THINK HE WENT FROM THERE TO
YOUNG AND THE RESTLESS.
I USED TO WATCH A LOT OF SOAP
OPERAS BACK IN THE DAY.
ANY WAY REST IN PEACE.
>> YEAH.
>>> NOW LET'S GO TO EMPIRE STAR
JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
HE PERFORMED FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE HE WAS THE VICTIM OF A
HORRIFIC ALLEGEDLY RACIALLY
MOTIVATED HATE CRIME ATTACK IN
CHICAGO LAST WEEK.
ON SATURDAY, IN LOS ANGELES,
SINGER -- SINGER AND ACTOR NOT
ONLY PERFORMED IN FRONT OF
HUNDREDS OF FANS, HE ALSO SPOKE
ABOUT THE INCIDENT.
SMOLLETT SAID HE WANTED TO USE
THIS OPPORTUNITY TO CLEAR UP A
FEW THINGS INCLUDING THAT HIS
RIBS WERE BRUISED, NOT CRACKED
OR BROKEN, HE ALSO SAID HE WAS
NOT HOSPITALIZED BECAUSE OF THE
ATTACK.
SMOLLETT TOLD THE CROWD HE'S
OKAY.
HE'S STILL HEALING FROM THE
ATTACK.
AND WHILE HE TOOK TO THE STAGE
AND PERFORMED HE DID GO AHEAD
AND CANCEL THE POST SHOW MEET
AND GREET WITH FANS WHICH IS
UNDERSTANDABLE.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT MANY RAPPER
21 SAVAGE HE'S FACING POSSIBLE
DEPORT TEAGUE.
IMMIGRATION AND CUSTOMS ARRESTED
THE MUSICIAN BORN SHIAA ABRAM
HAD A JOSEPH SUNDAY IN AT LAND
TAM ICE SAYS IT WAS PART OF A
TARGETED OPERATION.
ABRAHAM JOSEPH IS A BRITISH
CITIZEN.
HOW MANY PEOPLE KNEW THAT.
>> HE ENTERED THE COUNTRY
ILLEGAL UNTIL 2005 BUT FAILED TO
LEAVE WHEN HIS VISA WAS UP IN
2006.
21 STATUE RATCH PLACED INTO
REMOVAL PROCEEDINGS BEFORE THE
FEDERAL IMMIGRATION COURTS.
HE WAS NOMINATED FOR TWO A
AWARDS AT THE GRAMMYS NEXT WE
WEEK'S GRAMMYS.
>> HERE'S WHAT I DON'T GET.
A LOT OF QUESTIONS HERE.
BUT IF HE'S BEEN LIVING IN THIS
COUNTRY ILLEGALLY TO ARE 13
YEARS AND THEY TOUT HE'S BEEN
ARRESTED BEFORE ESPECIALLY IN
ATLANTA.
>> EXACTLY.
>> HOW IS THIS NEVER COME TO
REALIZATION OVER THE LAST 13
YEARS.
>> GOOD QUESTION.
>> ESPECIALLY IF HE'S GONE
THROUGH THE COURT SYSTEM.
>> VERY GOOD QUESTION.
AND CLEARLY YOU KNEW HE WAS
GOING TO BE IN ATLANTA.
>> SOMEONE IS TRYING TO MAKE A
POINT.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
>> TRYING TO MAKE AN EXAMPLE,
YEAH.
>>> LET'S TALK ABOUT DEMI LOW
HAVE THE TOW CAUGHT BACKLASH
AFTER MENTIONING THE ARREST OF
THE 21 SAVAGE.
>> PRODUCER CHRIS IS FOLLOWING
THIS ONE FROM THE FOX5 CONTROL
ROOM.
CHRIS WHAT HAPPENED.
>> SHE SHUT DOWN HER TWITTER
ACCOUNT BECAUSE SHE WAS POSTING
ABOUT THE MEMES THAT HAD COME
OUT ABOUT 21 SAVAGE.
SO IN NOW DELETED TWEET SHE SAID
SO FAR THE 21 SAVAGE MEMES HAVE
BEEN MY FAVORITE PART OF THE
SUPER BOWL.
TRYING TO MAKE A JOKE BUT SOME
OF 21 SAVAGE'S FANS WERE NOT
HAVING IT.
THEY WERE NOT UM AMUSED THEY
FELT LIKE THE SINGER WAS TAKING
CHEAP SHOTS AT SOMEONE ELSE'S
MISFORTUNE.
ONE OF THOSE FANS WHO CALLED HER
OUT ONLINE WAS D.C.'S OWN WALE.
SO HE POSTED A TWEET BASICALLY
WAY WHY IS SOMEBODY'S FREEDOM
FUNNY.
I DON'T GET THE JOKE.
SHE DID RESPOND TO THAT
BASICALLY DEFENDING HERSELF
SAYING THAT, YOU KNOW, SHE WAS
JUST LAUGHING ABOUT THE MEMES
NOT THE FACT THAT HE WAS GETTING
DEPORTED BY ANY MEANS.
BUT THEN SHE GOT A TON OF PEOPLE
BASICALLY THEN CALLING HER OUT
FOR HER OWN ADDICTION ISSUES AND
THE PROBLEMS SOME SHE HAD.
PEOPLE SAYING, YOU KNOW, NO ONE
WAS LAUGHING AT YOU WHEN THIS
WAS GOING ON OR IF THEY WERE,
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE APPRECIATED IT
VERY MUCH.
SHE HAD ENOUGH OF IT AND SHE
CANCELED HER ACCOUNT AFTER THAT.
>> HMM.
IT IS WEIRD THAT SHE WOULD JUMP
INTO THAT.
THAT'S A PRETTY SERIOUS ISSUE IF
YOU'RE -- YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
GETTING CAUGHT BY ICE AND
GETTING DEPORTED.
>> SHE WAS FAR FROM THE ONLY ONE
JOKING ABOUT THOSE MEMES ONLINE.
THERE WERE A LOT THAT POPPED UP
IMMEDIATELY.
>> LET ME SAY THIS.
I SAW ONE OF THOSE MEMES AND IT
WAS FUNNY TO ME.
I KNOW THAT IT'S NOT A LAUGHING
MATTER.
>> WAS IT THE BRITISH RED COAT
ONE.
>> YES.
A LOT OF THEM THAT WERE FUNNY.
>> I SAW THAT ONE, TOO.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY PEOPLE ARE
JUMPING ON DEMI LOVATO.
>> SHE'S FAMOUS.
>> BUT HERE'S THE THING.
SHE'S GOT ISSUES OF HER OWN.
>> WE HAVE TAKEN THIS THING TO
RIDICULOUS EXTENT.
YOU CAN'T EVEN LAUGH ANY MORE.
OF ONE KNOWS YOU'RE NOT LAUGHING
AT THIS MAN'S MISFORTUNE.
LET'S BE CLEAR.
>> SHE CAN'T LAUGH.
>> BUT WHY?
>> BECAUSE SHE'S GOT HER OWN --
WHY --
>> WE ALL HAVE OUR OWN ISSUES. .
YOUR OWN CURRENT ISSUES JUMP
INTO SOMEBODY ELSE'S ISSUE WHEN
IT COMES TO CUSTOMS?
>> HERE'S THE THING.
>> THAT'S THE PROBLEM I GOT WITH
IT.
>> I DON'T THINK SHE'S JUMPING
INTO SOMEONE'S ISSUE.
I THINK SHE SHE WAS SOMETHING
AND REACTED TO IT MAYBE WITHOUT
THINKING THE RAMIFICATIONS.
THE GIRL CAN'T EVEN POST
SOMETHING.
>> NO.
>> SHE'S A STAR.
SHE SHOULDN'T BE DOING THIS
SHE'S HAD ISSUES OF HER OWN.
I DON'T THINK IT'S FAIR.
>> SOCIAL MEDIA IS OPTIONAL.
>> I DON'T GET IT BUT I DON'T
THINK IT'S FAIR.
>> SHE MADE A CONSCIOUS EFFORT
TO GO IN THERE AND BE PETTY.
I'M SORRY.
SHE'S BEING PETTY.
THE OTHER PEOPLE, THEY'RE NOT
FAMOUS.
NOBODY CARES BUT IF YOU'RE
FAMOUS AND YOU GET --
>> A LOT OF FAMOUS PEOPLE
REPOSTED IT.
A LOT OF THEM DID.
>> SHE'S THE BIG FISH.
>> NOBODY WAS TELLING THEM
YOU'RE BEING UNSENSITIVE.
PEOPLE PICK ON PEOPLE I THINK
THEY THINK THEY CAN BECAUSE I'LL
TELL WAS, I DARE TO YOU SAY YOU
DIDN'T LAUGH AT ANYONE OF THOSE.
I DON'T KNOW THAT IT CAME FROM
MALICIOUS GREAT.
DEPORT HIM.
SOME OF THE MEMES WERE GENERALLY
FUNNY.
HAVING THIS GUY FAMOUS RAPPER
HERE WITH A BRITISH ACT ZEN
DOING ALL SORTS OF THINGS WITH
IT.
I DON'T THINK IT WAS MEANT IN A
MALICIOUS WAY FOR PEOPLE TO TAKE
IT THAT WAY AND ATTACK DEMI
LOVATO.
I DON'T THINK IT'S FAIR.
I'M NOT STANDING FOR HER.
IN GENERAL I DON'T THINK IT'S
FAIR TO TAX SOMEONE OVER A LOT
OF PEOPLE ARE LAUGHING OVER.
>> I THINK YOU NAILED IT WHEN
YOU SAID SOCIAL MEDIA IS UNFAIR.
>> I WOULDN'T JUMP INTO THAT.
THAT'S ALL I'M SAYING.
>> ARIANA, WHO.
>> PETE DAVIDSON HAD A SPECIAL
SOMEONE SPORTING HIM AT HIS
STANDUP SHOW IN LOS ANGELES THIS
WEEKEND.
SATURDAY NIGHT LIFE STEPPED OUT
WITH RUMORED FLAME KATE
BECKENSALE, DON'T GET IT.
DUO HELD HANDS AS THEY LEFT
FAMED MUSIC AND COMEDY VENUE
LARGO AT THE CORNET IN WEST
HOLLYWOOD.
HE PERFORMED AND INCLUDED IN A
SET SEVERAL JOKES ABOUT HIS EX
ARIANA GRANDE.
AFTER THE SHOW THEY WENT TO HIS
HOTEL IN SANTA MONICA THEY ONCE
AGAIN WERE SPOTTED HOLDING
HANDS.
THE STARS WERE FIRST SCENE
TOGETHER IN JANUARY WHEN THEY
HIT IT OFF AT NETFLIX GOLDEN
GLOBES AFTER PARTY.
ALL OF THIS PROVING THAT FUNNY
DUDES GET THE GIRLS.
I'M JUST SAYING.
>> MAYBE HE WAS JUST HOLDING
HER, STEVE, BACK ME UP ON THIS,
MAYBE HE WAS HOLDING HER HAND HE
DIDN'T WANT HER TO FALL AS SHE
WAS WALKING DOWN THE STREET.
BEING A GENTLEMAN.
>> PROBABLY DARK OUT.
>> AND THEY WENT UP TO THE ROOM
BECAUSE IT WAS MAYBE IT WAS A
LITTLE CHILLY OUTSIDE.
YOU KNOW HOW IT CAN GET ON THE
WEST COAST AT NIGHTTIME.
>> WHEN THEY REPORTED TO BE
MAKING OUT, WHAT HAPPENED HE
TRIPPED INTO HER.
>> IT'S HAPPENED.
>> MAKING SURE SHE DIDN'T HAVE
SOMETHING STUCK IN HER TEETH.
>> MAYBE SHE NEEDED THE HEIMLICH
MANEUVER.
>> OKAY.
>> FROM THE FRONT.
I'M JUST SAYING.
>> WE SEE.
>> IT'S ALL POSSIBLE WISDOM.
>> COMPLETELY POSSIBLE.
>> I'M JUST SAYING, PETE, YOU GO
ON WITH YOURSELF.
YOU GET THE HOT GIRLS.
>> KEEP DOING YOUR THING.
10:21.
>> CLEARLY.
>> MID WINTER WARMUP WE TALK
ABOUT LAST WEEK FINALLY ARRIVED.
>> TEMPERATURES THIS WEEK
CLIMBING INTO THE 50S.
60S, MAKE 70S.
WHAT IN THE WORLD?  TUCKER IS
BACK WITH THE DETAILS COMING UP
NEXT.
♪
[phone ringing]
Remember the way we
used to do things?
Hey man...
Like connect with friends?
Dig it!
Or get in shape?
Or sell a house
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
[crash]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
Show me The Crown.
than the one next door.
Show me Homecoming.
Baby sloth videos on YouTube.
Amy, do you uh mind giving
someone else a turn?
Oh yeah I made myself a
little comfortable here.
I got a pizza for Amy!
Yes, that's me!
Xfinity lets you search
Netflix, Prime Video,
and YouTube
with the sound of your voice.
And I don't have my wallet, so.
That's Simple.
Easy. Awesome.
Get started with Xfinity
Internet, TV and Voice for
$79.99 a month for 2 years,
plus ask about 4K Ultra HD.
Click, call or visit
a store today.
♪
>>> MANIC I COULDN'T CALL TODAY
MANIC.
>> LAST WEEK WAS MANIC.
>> YES.
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
YESTERDAY WASN'T BAD.
>> WAIT UNTIL TOMORROW.
>> EVEN BETTER.
>> YEAH.
>> GREAT.
TUCKER BARNES,.
>> MAYBE IT'S HEADACHE MONDAY
BECAUSE YOU HAD TOO MANY LAST
NIGHT WATCHING THE SUPER BOWL.
>> TOO MANY?
>> OH --
>> REJECTION.
>> I CAN'T RELATE.
>> HE DIDN'T DRINK OR WATCH THE
SUPER BOWL.
>> RIGHT.
>> IT TURNS OUT WISDOM YOU WERE
THE SMART TEST IN THE ENTIRE
GROUP.
RIGHT.
>> DIDN'T WASTE ANY TIME.
>> EXACTLY.
>> OKAY.
>> I MENTIONED EARLIER AT ONE
POINT I WENT TO GET SOMETHING
OUT OF MY CLOSET I WAS IN THERE
FOR 20 MINUTES.
I HAVEN'T SPENT MINUTES IN MY
CLOSET.
>> REARRANGING IT WANT NOT.
>> IN TEN YEARS.
I CAME OUT AND NOTHING HAD
HAPPENED.
THREE MORE PUNTS.
I WAS LIKE I'M NOT MISSING
ANYTHING HERE.
HEY, 40 NOW IN WASHINGTON.
WINDS OUT OF THE EAST AT THREE.
WE'RE GOING TO BELIEVE IT OR NOT
GET IT INTO THE UPPER 50S WE
MIGHT DO 60 DEGREES THIS
AFTERNOON VERY MILD TEMPERATURES
EXPECTED AND A NICE QUIET
FORECAST.
FEW CLOUDS HERE.
SOUTHERN MARYLAND LOWER EASTERN
SHORE ASSOCIATED WITH THAT
LITTLE AREA OF LOW PRESSURE BUT
THIS IS BEING PUSHED OUT TO SEA
IT WON'T IMPACT US, AND WE'RE
ALL SYSTEMS GO FOR NOT ONLY VERY
VERY NICE MONDAY AFTERNOON, BUT
A NICE COUPLE OF DAYS TO LOOK
FORWARD TO, AS WE GET THAT FRONT
NORTH OF US.
WE'LL GET OUR WINDS OUT OF THE
SOUTH AND WEST.
AND FOR THE TIME BEING, NOT JUST
DC NOT JUST MID ATLANTIC, BUT
REALLY UP AND DOWN THE EASTERN
SEABOARD TEMPERATURES WELL ABOVE
NORMAL AROUND HERE FOR THE NEXT
COUPLE OF DAYS.
SO WE'LL BE UPPER 50S MAYBE WE
GET TO 60 TODAY.
THAT WOULD BE 15 DEGREES ABOVE
NORMAL AND MID 60S TOMORROW.
COULD A SPOT OR TWO MAKE A RUN
AT 70 TOMORROW?  I THINK SO.
AS WE'RE GOING TO BE IN FOR
INCREDIBLY MILD AIR FOR THIS
TIME OF YEAR AND WHAT A
DIFFERENCE FROM A FEW DAYS AGO
WHEN WE HAD TEMPERATURES NEAR
ZERO.
LOOK AT THAT.
WELL ABOVE NORMAL THROUGH THE
END OF THE WEEK.
SOME SHOWERS AROUND WEDNESDAY,
THURSDAY AND FRIDAY.
I DO WANT TO THE MENTION THE
COOLER TEMPS COME BACKS NEXT
WEEK.
NOT ALL SYSTEMS GO FOR SPRING
BUT BILL OASIS IN OTHER TIME --
OTHERWISE WINTERTIME PATTERN.
>> I LIKE THAT.
OASIS.
>> VERY POETIC.
>> OASIS IN ANOTHER TIME WINTER
PATTERN.
>> YEAH.
>> I WROTE THAT MYSELF.
PRETTY GOOD.
>> VERY NICE.
VERY NICE, TUCKER.
TEN COT 26 IS THE TIME.
THE WAIT IS ALMOST OVER FOR FANS
OF THE LEGO MOVIE.
THE NEW SEQUEL THE SECOND PART
HITS THEATERS THIS WEEKEND.
FIRST, THOUGH, KEVIN GOT PART
TWO OF HIS INTERVIEW WITH STARS
CHRIS PRATT AND ELIZABETH BANKS.
WE'LL SHOW IT TO YOU WHEN WE
COME BACK.
♪
This is Charlie not coughing
because he took Delsym 12-hour.
And this is Charlie still not
coughing
while trying his hardest not to
wake Zeus.
Delsym 12-hour.
Nothing lasts
longer for powerful
cough relief.
My mom washes the dishes...
...before she puts them in the
dishwasher.
So what does the dishwasher do?
Cascade Platinum does the work
for you,
prewashing and removing
stuck-on foods,
the first time.
Wow, that's clean!
Cascade Platinum.
You've got to get in
there, like...
I know what a bath is
Smile Honey
This thing is like...
First Kid
Ready
Here we go
By their second kid, every
parent is an expert and...
...more likely to choose Luvs,
than first time parents.
Live, Learn and get Luvs
♪
>>> WE WANT SODA.
>> LUCY,.
>> BATMAN SUPERMAN?
>> THE TIN MAN.
>> AND RUTH BADER GINSBURG.
LEGO MOVIE TWO RATED PG.
YOU CAN EXPERIENCE IT IN I MAX.
>> THAT'S A CLIP FROM THE LEGO
MOVIE THE SECOND PART.
IT'S A SEQUEL TO THE 2014 BOX
OFFICE HIT AND REUNITED STARS
CHRIS PRATT ELIZABETH BANKS AND
WILL ARNETT.
KEVIN GOT A CHANCE TO CATCH UP
ALL WITH ALL THE STARS AND JOINS
US WITH THE DETAILS.
>> I DID.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LAST WEEK WE AIRED CHRIS PRATT
PART ONE.
CHRIS PART TALKED ABOUT -- I
CONGRATULATED HIM ENNUIS
ENGAGEMENT TALKED ABOUT THE
SOCIAL MEDIA COMMAND MANY THAT
HE USES BEFORE HE POSTS ON&
SOCIAL MEDIA.
>> HE ACTUALLY THINKS ABOUT IT
BEFORE HE GOES ON THERE.
>> YEAH.
THE MOVIE DEALS WITH A GOOD
THEME OF THIS IDEA THE WORLD HAS
SO MUCH NEG NEGATIVITY IN IT.
>> WE CHANGE OURSELVES AND WE
WANT TO GUARD OURSELVES FROM
NEGATIVE VAL.
I ASKED HIM ABOUT THAT HARDING
HIMSELF AND BEING THAT EXCITING
PERSON THAT HE IS.
THIS PARTICULAR INTERVIEW HE
TALKS ABOUT THIS IDEA OF
BROODING IN MOVIES.
>> OKAY.
>> ACTORS GET INTO THAT BROODING
MOMENT THEY'RE VERY SERIOUS.
>> I DO THE EVERY DAY AT
4:00 O'CLOCK WHEN I COME IN
HERE.
>> EXACTLY.
I SPOKE TO ELIZABETH BANKS AND
CHRIS PRATT ABOUT THE ART OF
BROODING IN A FILM FILL LORD AND
CHRIS MILLER THE WRITERS AND PRO
DOUSE SEARS YOU'LL FIND OUT HOW
THEY GOT RUTH BADER GINSBURG TO
BE IN THE LEGO MOVIE TWO.
WATCH THIS.
>> HEY LUCY.
>> I BROUGHT YOU COFFEE.
>> COFFEE.
THE BITTER LIQUID THAT PROVIDES
THE ONLY SEEM BLANKS OF PLEASURE
LEFT IN THESE DARK TIMES.
>> MY GOSH.
DID I INTERRUPT YOU BROODING.
>> THE PEFECT BROOD.
LOOKING BACK AT YOUR EARLIER
FILMS WHAT DO YOU THINK IS YOUR
BEST BROODING MOMENT IN A MOVIE
YOU'VE DONE.
>> OOH, HOW BROOD -- I'M NOT
TYPICALLY A BROODY CHARACTER.
>> I'M NOT SUPER BROOD Y ON
SURVEILLANCE JURASSIC LOOK OFF
IN THE DISTANT AND IMAGINE THE
ROOM IS REALLY SMOKY.
>> TOTALLY.
>> IS THERE AN ART FORM TO THE
BROOD.
I LOVE THE SEQUENCE OF YOUR
CHARACTER IN THE BEGINNING.
>> IT'S ABOUT THE VOICE.
REALLY, REALLY DROP YOUR VOICE
DOWN AND TALK QUIETLY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> VERY SERIOUS.
>> YEAH.
>> WHO ARE YOU?
>> THE NAME IS REX, GALAXY
DEFENDING ARCHAEOLOGIST, COWBOY
AND RAPTOR TRAINER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I DON'T GET IT.
>> WHEN DO YOU EMMITT AND REX IN
SEQUENCE TOGETHER AND THEY'RE
HAVING A CONVERSATION DO YOU
ACTUALLY DO THE CONVERSATION IN
FULL IN THE BOOTH OR DO YOU DO
THEM INDIVIDUALLY.
>> I DO THEM INDIVIDUALLY.
EASIER FOR TIME FOR ME TO GO
THROUGH AND DO ALL MY EMMITT
STUFF AND GO BACK THROUGH AND DO
ALL OF MY REX STUFF.
>> OKAY.
>> AND SO ESPECIALLY THE
BEGINNING OF THE PROCESS BECAUSE
I WASN'T SUPER FAMILIAR WITH
DOING REX'S VOICE.
IT WAS HARD TO GO BACK AND
FORTH.
BUT TOWARDS THE END, I FIND
IT -- I FIND I CAN DO IT NOW.
I CAN GO BACK AND FORTH.
I'M MAKING A BUNCH OF VIDEOS ON
INSTAGRAM GOING BACK AND FORTH
BETWEEN THE VOICES IT'S NOT HARD
AS NOW AS IT WOULD HAVE BEEN A
YEAR OR TWO AGO WHEN WE CAME UP
WITNESS THE CHARACTER.
>> I WANTED TO ASK YOU ABOUT THE
RB.
GOOD THING.
MIKE RELEASED A QUOTE ABOUT THEY
REACHED OUT TO HER ACTUAL TEAM.
HOW DID THAT WORK?  I KNOW SHE
HAS A VOICE.
>> YES.
>> HOW DO YOU GET APPROVE TO DO
A LEGO FIGURINE OF HER.
>> WHO WOULD BE A FUN PERSON TO
BE IN THE WEDDING PARTY THAT
BIANCA WOULD LIKE AS A FIGURINE.
WHAT ABOUT RUTH BADER GINSBURG.
THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY ASK HER IF
IT'S OKAY.
>> WHAT DO YOU DO?  DO YOU
REACH -- DO YOU ACTUALLY E-MAIL
HER.
>> WE'RE SO IRRESPONSIBLE.
SITTING IN COFFEE SHOP GOING,
RUTH BADER GUNS BURG.
>> THAT SOUNDS FUN.
>> OTHER PEOPLE HAVE TO FIGURE
IT ALL OUT.
>> A BUILDING FULL OF LAWYERS
THAT HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> THEY'RE THE REAL HEROES OF
THIS STORY.
THE BUSINESS AFFAIRS PEOPLE AND
THE LAWYERS.
>> INTERESTING THING ABOUT THAT
SHE HAS NO LINES IN THE FILM
RUTH BADER GUNS BURG THEY HAD TO
ACTUALLY GET THE PERMISSION JUST
TO USE HER LIKENESS AND THEY
WERE ACTUALLY I BELIEVE GOING TO
SELL THE RUTH BADER GUNS BURG
LEGO FIGURINE WHICH IS PRETTY
COOL.
YOU HEARD CHRIS PRATT IN THE
INTERVIEW TALK ABOUT THIS IDEA
IN THE MOVIE HE PLAYS TWO
CHARACTERS.
HE PLEA US EMMITT AND HE PLAYS
REX THE TWO CHARACTERS YOU SAW
TALKING TO EACH OTHER IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE PACKAGE THERE.
I WANTED TO AND IF HE VOICED
THEM TOGETHER ONSET.
NOW THAT I'M DOING INSTAGRAM
VIDEOS I'VE NOW BEEN ABLE TO DO
BOTH THEIR VOICES AND HERE'S THE
INSTAGRAM VIDEO HE'S TALKING
ABOUT.
>> IT'S STARRING ME, REX DANGER
FEST.
>> AND ME, TECH ANY KLEE.
>> NO.
MOSTLY ME.
>> I JUST THINK THAT WE'RE
BETTER IF WE STICK TOGETHER.
>> ♪
>> HE GOES ON AND DOES ALL THESE
FUNNY INSTAGRAM VIDEOS.
WHAT'S CRAZY ABOUT I DIDN'T SAY
PRATT IF YOU WATCH THIS VIDEO HE
PLAYS WIG LEGO FIGURINES OF HIS
CHARACTERS PLAYING OVER THE PAST
FIVE YEARS.
THINK ABOUT HOW ICONIC THE
CHARACTERS HE'S PLAYING NOW.
HE HAS EMMITT IN LEGO MOVIE NOW
REX.
HE ALSO HAS THE CHARACTER FROM
JURASSIC WORLD WHO YOU SAW ON
THE RAPTOR THERE HE HAS STAR
LORD OF GUARDIAN OF THE GALAXY.
A GUY WHO HAS PROBABLY ONE OF
THE BEST FILMOGRAPHIES TODAY AND
HE'S IN THE AVENGERS MOVIES.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S A BIG DEAL.
>> NOT BAD.
>> HE HAS A HUGE BOX OFFICER
OFFICE NUMBER RIGHT NOW.
>> LOTS OF CHECKS COMING IN.
>> THAT MOVIE OPENS FRIDAY.
A HUGE HIT OBVIOUSLY ALL THE
KIDS AND FAMILIES WILL SEE IT
THIS WEEKEND.
I'LL HAVE THE REVIEW FRIDAY
MORNING.
I LIKE IT A LOT.
BIG FAN OF LEGO MOVIES.
FULL REVIEW THIS COMING FRIDAY.
>> KEVIN, MAYBE IT WAS THE THAW
THAT POLAR VORTEX OR THE BIG
GAME.
PEOPLE ARE NOT FLOCKING TO THE
MOVIE THEATERS.
>> THIS PAST WEEKEND.
>> IN FACT, IT WAS THE SLOWEST
SUPER BOWL WEEKEND AT THE BOX
OFFICE IN NEARLY 20 YEARS.
>> YEAH.
>> 20 YEARS.
NOW THE PEOPLE WHO DID MAKE IT
TO THE MOVIE, WELL, THEY WERE
SPENDING THEIR MONEY ON GLASS
THE MOVIE --
>> I DID NOT LIKE GLASS.
>> IT'S STILL MAKING A LOT OF
MONEY THOUGH.
>> IN FACT IT EARNED A LITTLE
LESS THAN $10 MILLION THAT WAS
STILL ENOUGH FOR THE TOP SPOT.
THAT MAKES THREE STRAIGHT WEEKS
AT NUMBER ONE FOR THE M KNIGHT
SHYAMALAN THRILLER DESPITE MIXED
TO NEGATIVE REVIEWS.
>> YOU GOT TO REMEMBER THESE
MOVE MOVIES ESPECIALLY --
>> YOU'VE SEEN THE REST OF THEM.
>> RIGHT THERE.
>> GLASS DIDN'T COST A LOT OF
MONEY TO MAKE.
IT MADE A TON OF MONEY.
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN LISTEN SUPER BOWL
WEEKEND THAT IS THE LOWEST IN 20
YEARS AS THE SCRIPT SAID.
NOTHING REALLY HUGE OPENED.
MISS BALA OPENED THAT WAS PRETTY
MUCH IT.
THIS PARTICULAR WEEKEND COMING
UP, THOUGH, IT WILL BE HUGE.
LEGO MOVIE, ALSO HAVE THIS LIAM
NEESEN CALLED COLD PURSUIT.
>> I'VE SEEN THE TRAILERS.
>> ALSO TARAJI P. HENSON SON
MOVIE.
>> WHAT MEN WANT.
THE REMAKE OR REIMAGINING OF THE
MEL GIBSON MOVIE WHAT WOMEN W
WANT.
I ONCE TRIED A LITTLE
EXPERIMENT.
IF I GO TO THE THEATER FRIDAY
WITH MY WOMEN WANT TICKET CAN I
GET IN.
>> ISSUED VIDEO THAT.
>> SIR, STEP THIS WAY.
I WENT TOLL BATHROOM.
THIS IS MY TICKET STUB.
THAT'S FROM NEWPORT NEWS, SAVAGE
THAT'S NOT D.C.
>> HOLLY, OVER TO YOU.
>> HEY, KEV.
>> YEAH.
>> KEV, I DON'T THINK THE LIAM
NEESEN MOVIE WILL OPEN AT NUMBER
ONE.
DO YOU KNOW WHY.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> IT LICENSE TAKE WINE ANOTHER
MOVIE.
>> I KNEW IT.
>> THE TOP SPOT WILL BE TAKEN.
>> IT WILL BE TAKEN BY ANOTHER
MOVIE.
>> TOP SPOT WILL BE TAKEN BY
LEGO MOVIE.
>> GOOD JOB, KEV, FIGURING IT
OUT.
WE HAVE ONE MORE ENTERTAINMENT
STORY FOR YOU.
KYLIE JENNER STOKING RUMORS
SHE'S CONSIDERING AFTER ANOTHER
BABY WITH TRAVIS SCOTT.
IN INSTAGRAM POST THEY SHARED A
PHOTO TAKEN WITH HER PARTNER
SCOTT ALONG WITH AN EXTREMELY
SUGGESTIVE CAPTION WRITING ONLY,
BABY NUMBER TWO?
JENNER MUST HAVE HAVE KNOWN
EVERYONE ON THE INTERNET WOULD
BE INSTANTLY SHOOK ESPECIALLY AS
THE FIRST COUPLE'S STORM MY
CELEBRATED HER FIRST BIRTHDAY.
COULD THIS MEAN THAT BABY NUMBER
TWO IS ALREADY ON THE WAY FOR
JENNER AND SCOTT?
>> I CAN HARDLY WAIT TO KNOW.
>> WE SHALL SEE.
>> 10:37 RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
FROM PLAYING BACKUP FOR ALICIA A
KARA TO TALKING THE SPOTLIGHT
RIGHT HERE IN D.C., SINGER CRAIG
STICKLAND JOINS US LIVE.
>> LATER THE PERFECT VALENTINE'S
DAY GIFT FOR ANYONE WITH A
SWEETHEART -- WITH A SWEET
TOOTH.
WE'RE LEARNING HOW TO MAKE HOME
LAID CHOCOLATE TRUFFLES.
YUM ! THAT'S COMING UP NEXT.
10:37 IS OUR TIME.
♪
♪♪
♪ 'Cos I know what it means ♪
♪ To walk along the lonely
street of dreams ♪
♪ Here I go again on my--- ♪
You realize your vows are a
Whitesnake song?
I do.
If you ride, you get it.
GEICO Motorcycle.
15 minutes
could save you 15% or more.
My gums are irritated.
I don't have to worry about
that, do I?
Actually, you do.
Harmful bacteria lurk just below
the gum line.
New Crest Gum Detoxify works
below the gum line
to neutralize harmful plaque
bacteria
and help reverse early gum
damage.
Gum Detoxify, from Crest.
When your blanket's freshness
fades
before the binge-watching
begins...
that's when you know,
it's half-washed.
Next time,
add Downy Fabric Conditioner
for up to 7 days of Downy
freshness.
Downy and it's done.
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
♪
>>> GOOD SOUND.
OUR NEXT GUEST SPENT TWO YEARS
CRISS-CROSSING NORTH AMERICA IN
CONVERTED VAN IN PERFORMING AS A
GUITARIST FOR ALICIA AKARA.
THAT TIME INSPIRED CHRIS
STICKLAND TO SELF PRODUCE HIS
UPCOMING SOPHOMORE ALBUM STARLIT
AFTERNOON.
AND NOW HE'S BACK ON THE ROAD
AND HE'S TAKING THE STAGE AT
CITY WINERY RIGHT HERE IN D.C.
FIRST THOUGH THIS MORNING HE IS
LIVE IN THE LOFT.
SO HERE TO PERFORM HIS LATEST
SINGLE "BURN IT DOWN" PLEASE
WELCOME, CRAIG STICK LAND.
♪
>> ANY TIME IS A TIME FOR
CELEBRATION, ANY DAY IS A DAY
FOR VACATION, I'M ALIVE AND FEEL
LIKE GETTING HIGH ♪
>> ♪ COLORADO, ARIZONA, VEGAS,
EVERYWHERE I MAKING FRIENDS WITH
STRANGERS, EVERYBODY WANTS TO
GET INSPIRED ♪
>> ♪ OH, WHEN CASE FEEL RIGHT
PASS ME THE LIGHT, WE GOT TO
BURN IT DOWN UNTIL THE SKY ♪
>> ♪
♪
>> ♪ BURN IT DOWN, BABE ♪
>> ♪
♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I LOVE EVERYTHING ABOUT YOUR
SOUND.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING IN
THIS MORNING.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> AS CLEARLY THE ONLY ONE IN
THE LOT OF THAT HAS REAL MUSIC
TALENT, WE'RE DYING TO KNOW WHAT
YOUR OPINION OF THE SUPER BOWL
HALF TIME SHOW WAS.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, I ACTUALLY
DRIVING THE ENTIRE TIME.
>> YOU MISSED IT.
>> I MIFF THE WHOLE THING.
>> YOU DIDN'T MISS A THING.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT YOU.
YOU HAVE SUCH AN AMAZING STORY.
HOW DID YOU GET HOOKED UP WITH
ALICIA.
>> WE HAVE THE SAME MANAGEMENT
ACTUALLY.
>> THAT WORKS.
>> YOU BET.
>> THAT WORK.
THEN YOU'RE PERFORMING WITH HER
OPENING FOR COLD PLAY.
WHAT WAS ALL THAT LIKE?
FAVORITE COLD PLAY STORY.
>> MAN, ONCE IN A LIFETIME
EXPERIENCE.
MY FAVORITE COLD -- I CAN'T
REALLY PINPOINT A FAVORITE.
I THINK EVERY TIME JUST WATCHING
THEM PLAY WAS SO INSPIRING.
I HAVE TO GET THERE AFTER
WITNESSING THAT.
>> YOU KNOW YOU ARE GETTING
THERE.
YOU ARE DOING IT IN A VERY
UNIQUE WAY.
SO TELL ME ABOUT THE CONVERTED
SPRINTER VAN.
>> YES.
I STARTED TO CONVERT A SPRINTER
VAN INTO A FULLY SUSTAINABLE
SOLAR POWERED TOUR BUS.
>> JUST BECAUSE?
>> WELL BECAUSE I KNEW I HAD A
LOT OF TOURS COMING UP AND I
WANTED TO BE ABLE TO DO IT ON MY
OWN AND DO THE LOCAL THING SO
ALSO WE SHOT, SOLAR POWERED, UM,
VERSIONS OF EVERY SONG OFF MY
ALBUM AS WELL.
>> I WAS WATCHING SOME OF THE
VIDEO.
IT'S SO COOL.
WHERE YOU PERFORMED AND SHOT
THESE WERE AMAZING.
>> YEAH.
>> SOME OF MY FAVORITE PLACES
ALL OVER.
>> NAME A FEW FOR PEOPLE WHO
DON'T KNOW.
>> YOSEMITE WE BROUGHT PIANO TO
YOSEMITE.
ALABAMA HILLS WHICH IS JUST BASE
OF MOUNTAINS AND BIG SIR
CALIFORNIA.
>> JOSH WITNESS TREE ALL OVER
THE PLACE.
>> DOING IT BIG.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S BEEN GOOD.
>> TELL ME ABOUT YOUR TOUR NOW.
I KNOW YOU RELEASED THIS SONG.
>> THE FIRST SINGLE OFF OF MY
ALBUM SO WEARY LEASING A SINGLE
EVERY MONTH LEADING UP TO I
THINK IT'S JULY 26th.
THE ALBUM WILL BE COMING OUT AND
RIGHT NOW ON TOUR WITH HUDSON
TAYLOR AND WE'RE AT THE CITY
WINERY TONIGHT.
>> GREAT VENUE.
D.C. CITY WINERY GREAT VENUE.
I THINK YOU'RE GOING TO LIKE IT.
YOU SAID YOU WANT TO GET THERE
ONE DAY LIKE A COLD PLAY.
WHAT DO YOU SEE AS YOUR JOURNEY,
YOUR PATH?
>> I THINK JUST LIVING OUT OF
THE VAN AND THEN MOVING TO A
TOUR BUS AND --
>> YEAH.
>> MOVING UP FROM A SPRINTER
VAN.
>> THERE'S SO MUCH CHARACTER
WITH THE CONVERTED SPRINTER VAN.
>> MAYBE THE VAN WILL RIGHT
BEHIND THE BUS.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> IT NEEDS TO ALWAYS BE A PART
OF YOUR STORY.
THAT'S WHAT INK OOH.
YOU KNOW WHAT I LOVE ABOUT YOU
TOO,.
HERE YOU ARE.
I MEAN YOU'VE WRITTEN, PRODUCED,
YOU PERFORMED THESE SONGS.
YOU'RE ENERGIZING THEM WITH YOUR
SOLAR SPRINTER VAN.
BUT FOR YOU WHEN I WAS READING
ABOUT YOU, EVERY SONG REALLY IS
AN EXPERIENCE.
YOU IT NEEDS TO BE AN
EXPERIENCE.
>> UM-HMM.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT.
>> I THINK THAT I ALWAYS FELL IN
LOVE WITH MUSIC THAT TOOK ME ON
A JOURNEY.
LIKE COLD PLAY, FOR EXAMPLE,
WHEN YOU'RE LISTENING TO
SOMETHING FROM BEGINNING TO END
YOU'RE REALLY FEELING A WHOLE
RANGE OF EMOTIONS THAT'S WHAT I
TRY AND CREATE WITH MY MUSIC.
SO A LOT OF SONGS WILL START
VERY INTIMATE WITH JUST ME AND
THE GUITAR AND WE'LL GROW TO A
HUGE SOUND SCAPE WITH HUNDRED
INSTRUMENTS GOING ON.
>> I SEE NOTHING BUT GREAT
THINGS HEADED YOUR WAY.
>> AWESOME.
>> TICKETS STILL AVAILABLE FOR
TONIGHT.
>> I THINK AT THE DOOR A FEW,
YEAH.
>> A FEW.
THEY'RE GOING FAST AS YOU CAN
IMAGINE.
BUT THIS IS JUST THE BEGINNING
FOR YOU.
THOUGH YOU'RE ALREADY ON YOUR
WAY.
WHAT AM I TALKING ABOUT.
REMEMBER US.
YOU CAN STILL PULL THAT TOUR BUS
IN OUR LOT WHEN YOU MAKE IT BIG.
> YOU GOT IT.
>> BEST OF LUCK.
MAUREEN, OVER TO YOU.
>> PERFECT.
VALENTINE'S DAY JUST TEN DAYS
AWAY AND IF YOU LOVE CHOCOLATE,
THOUGHTFUL GIFT IDEA YOU MIGHT
HAVE YOU COVERED WITH THE
PERFECT PRE-VALENTINE'S DAY
ACTIVITY WILLARD INTER
CONTINENTAL TEA TEAMING UP WITH
SPANK VOLE LA TO HELP TEACH ME
HOW TO MAKE HOMEMADE CHOCOLATE
TRUFFLES.
JANET SCANLON IS HERE ALONG WITH
MASTER CHOCOLATIER CO-FOUNDER
CHRIS REID AND HER HUSBAND ERIC.
ERIC REID THAT'S RIGHT.
SO NOW THIS COUPLE THEY'RE
UNIQUE THAT THAT THEY DON'T JUST
MAKE THE TRUFFLES.
THEY'RE ALL INTO THE SOIL AND
WHAT MAKES A WONDERFUL CHOC
CHOCOLATE.
AND THEY'RE GOING TO TEACH US
ALL ABOUT THAT IN JUST A MINUTE.
WELCOME TO ALL OF YOU.
BUT I WANT TO START WITH YOU
JANET.
WILLARD INTER CONTINENTAL GIVING
PEOPLE THIS OPPORTUNITY.
TELL US ABOUT IT.
>> GOOD MORNING.
THANKS FOR HAVING US.
>> YES.
>> SO THIS IS SATURDAY WE WILL
BE HAVING A CHOCOLATE TRUFFLE
MAKING CLASS AT THE WILLARD.
IT'S PART OF OUR MONTH LONG
CELEBRATION FOR VALENTINE'S DAY.
WE HAVE A LOT GOING ON.
WE HAVE A FOUR COURSE MENU AT
OUR RESTAURANT.
WE HAVE A CHAMPAGNE CART.
>> OH WOW.
>> MIXOLOGY CLASS AND OF COURSE,
A CHOCOLATE CLASS.
>> YES.
>> WITH THE MOST AMAZING
CHOCOLATE MAKERS OUT OF
GAITHERSBURG.
SO IF YOU ATTEND THE CLASS ON
SATURDAY THEY'LL BE LEARNING HOW
TO ROLL SOME TRUFFLES AND CHRIS
WILL BE ABLE TO GIVE YOU A HANDS
ON DEMO OF WHAT THEY'LL LEARN.
>> CHRIS AND ERIC, HOW LONG HAVE
YOU BEEN IN THE TRUFFLE MAKING
BUSINESS?
>> WE'VE BEEN BUSINESS NOR ABOUT
EIGHT YEARS.
>> RIGHT.
>> SO THE 12th OF THIS MONTHS
IS ACTUALLY OUR EIGHTH YEAR
ANNIVERSARY.
>> THIS IS SOMETHING THAT YOU
GUYS KIND OF GOT INTO FROM
SPAGNOLA IS A CARIBBEAN NAME
FROM DOMINICAN REPUBLIC.
>> THAT IS CORRECT.
>> WHAT DOES IT MEAN AND WHAT
WAS IT ABOUT THIS WHOLE
CHOCOLATE MAKING THING WE WANT
TO GET IN.
>> MY WIFE IS FROM THE DOMINICAN
REPUBLIC AND I'M FROM PANAMA.
WHEN WE MET WE FELL IN LOVE WITH
AIG CHER.
WE STARTED TO GROW OUR OWN COCOA
BEANS.
WE DECIDED TO INTEGRATE OUR
COCOA FROM OUR OWN FARM INTO THE
WORLD'S BEST CHOCOLATE.
>> THIS IS WHAT WE'RE GOING TO
SAMPLE.
OKAY.
CHRIS, YOU'LL TEACH US WHAT IT
IS WE'RE GOING TO DO WITH
TRUFFLES.
FIRST OF ALL, TRUFFLES ARE THEY
JUST CHOCOLATE OR A SPECIAL KIND
OF HACK LAT?  WHAT ARE TRUFFLES?
>> TRUFFLE IS, UM, MADE WITH
HEAVY CREAM.
>> UM-HMM.
>> BEGAN NASH, HEAVY CREAM AND
THE FLAVOR YOU LIKE TO INFUSE.
>> YOU'VE DONE IT TODAY WITH --
>> WITH ROSE PETALS.
>> OOH.
>> DID YOU EVER THINK ABOUT
THAT, TALK ABOUT SOMETHING
DECADENT FOR YOUR SWEETHEART.
ROSE PETALS.
>> THAT'S ALREADY IN HERE.
>> IT'S ALREADY IN HERE.
>> OKAY.
NORMALLY WE MAKE THE BEGAN NASH
BUT WE DON'T HAVE THE TIME.
>> IT'S PRE-MADE.
>> PRE-MADE.
COOP A LITTLE OUT.
>> SCOOP.
AND ROLL.
>> LIKE YOU'RE ROLLING A MEET
BALL.
>> YES.
>> OKAY.
>> HAVE YOUR CHOCOLATE ALREADY
TEMPERED AND JUST DIP IN THE
CHOCOLATE.
>> OKAY.
>> LOOK AT THAT.
>> AND THIS LITTLE THING SHE HAS
LITTLE GADGET IT LOOKS LIKE A
WHISKER BUT IT'S NOT.
LOOK AT THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
>> NOW YOU GARNISH.
>> HANG ON A SECOND.
YOU GARNISH.
ERIC WALK US THROUGH THIS.
>> SURE.
>> YOU MAKE DIFFERENT TYPES OF
TRUFFLES.
>> ABSOLABSOLUTELY.
>> HOW MANY DIFFERENT VARIETIES
DO YOU HAVE.
>> 12 DIFFERENT TYPES OF
TRUFFLES AND 12 DIFFERENT BON
BONES MADE WITH CHOCOLATE BEGAN
NASH.
THIS ONE ACTUALLY MADE WITH
AROSE CHAMPAGNE OR ROSE WINE
ACTUALLY ROSE WINE INFUSED WITH
JAZZ MINUTE AND THEN -- YUP.
DROP IT IN.
>> DROP IT IN.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> I WATCHED THE TECHNIQUE.
>> CHRIS, I WATCHED YOU.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> OKAY.
>> CHRIS, I WATCHED YOU.
YOU WANT TO -- OKAY.
>> OKAY.
>> PICK IT UP.
YOU WANT TO -- OKAY.
>> I GOT THIS.
>> PICK IT UP.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> I GOT THIS.
>> AND JUST FLIP IT OVER.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> OH.
>> AND JUST FLIP IT OVER.
OKAY.
>> OH.
>> SEE.
OKAY.
THERE YOU GO.
>> SEE.
>> GOOD JOB.
THERE YOU GO.
GOOD JOB.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> GOT A SECOND DREAR GOING H
GOOD JOB.
HERE.
>> GOT A SECOND DREAR GOING H
>> MOONLIGHT NOW AT A CHOCOLATE
HERE.
SHOP.
>> MOONLIGHT NOW AT A CHOCOLATE
>> AND SO WHEN PEOPLE COME TO
SHOP.
THE CLASS THEY'LL LEARN EXACTING
>> AND SO WHEN PEOPLE COME TO
THIS TECHNIQUE OR LEARN HOW TO
THE CLASS THEY'LL LEARN EXACTING
MAKE THIS BEFORE, YOU KNOW, THE
THIS TECHNIQUE OR LEARN HOW TO
WHOLE PROCESS.
MAKE THIS BEFORE, YOU KNOW, THE
>> WE TEACH THEM THE WHOLE
WHOLE PROCESS.
PROCESS.
>> WE TEACH THEM THE WHOLE
>> WOW.
PROCESS.
>> THERE'S STILL ROOM AVAILABLE.
>> WOW.
>> THERE ARE STILL TICKETS
>> THERE'S STILL ROOM AVAILABLE.
AVAILABLE.
>> THERE ARE STILL TICKETS
IT'S THREE TO FIVE ON SATURDAY.
AVAILABLE.
HOPEFULLY COME ON OUT.
IT'S THREE TO FIVE ON SATURDAY.
EVEN IF YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
HOPEFULLY COME ON OUT.
ABOUT CHOCOLATE MIKE MYSELF I DO
EVEN IF YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING
LIKE TO EAT IT.
ABOUT CHOCOLATE MIKE MYSELF I DO
AFTER WE PLACED IT ON THIS
LIKE TO EAT IT.
BEAUTIFUL WHITE CHINA CAN WE EAT
AFTER WE PLACED IT ON THIS
IT OR DOES IT HAVE TO COOL.
BEAUTIFUL WHITE CHINA CAN WE EAT
>> TYPICALLY YOU WOULD LET IT
IT OR DOES IT HAVE TO COOL.
COOL UNTIL IT HEART DENSE.
>> TYPICALLY YOU WOULD LET IT
IT WILL TAKE TIME HERE IN THE
COOL UNTIL IT HEART DENSE.
STUDIO.
IT WILL TAKE TIME HERE IN THE
IF YOU WANT TO GRAB ONE AND TRY
STUDIO.
IT, IT WOULD BE GREAT.
IF YOU WANT TO GRAB ONE AND TRY
>> ONE OF THESE?
IT, IT WOULD BE GREAT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> ONE OF THESE?
>> I'LL TRY THE ONE THAT CHRIS
>> ABSOLUTELY.
DID.
>> I'LL TRY THE ONE THAT CHRIS
>> YOU GOT IT.
DID.
DO THE WHOLE THING.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> OH, LORD.
HANG ON LET'S NOT MAKE A PLEAT
MESS HERE.
>> HMM.
OKAY.
HMM.
>> VERY DECADENT.
>> OH MY GOSH THAT IS SO RICH
AND CHOCOLATEY.
THIS IS AMAZING.
PUT THAT INFORMATION UP ONE MORE
TIME.
WILLARD INTERNATIONAL DOING IT
RIGHT FOR VALENTINE'S DAY.
IF YOUR SWEETHEART LOVES HACK
LAT THIS IS THE PLACE YOU HAVE
TO BE.
OH, MY GOSH, YOU GUYS.
WHERE ARE YOU LOCATED.
>> GAITHERSBURG MARYLAND.
IN THE COMMUNITY OF THE COAT
LANDS.
WE'VE BEEN THERE FOR EIGHT YE
YEARS.
CHECK US OUT.
>> SHORT TRIP UP 270.
>> THIS IS LIKE CHOCOLATE --
DEATH BY CHOCOLATE.
I'M LOVING EVERY MINUTE.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH GUYS.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> WE'LL INDULGE, THE WHOLE CREW
IS.
IN THE MEANTIME WE'LL BE BACK
AFTER THIS.
HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY IN
ADVANCE, EVERYBODY.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
Mascara in a snap.
New Snapscara from
Maybelline New York.
Smooth, clump-free volume.
Pure pigment formula means...
it's on & off in a snap!
No raccoon eyes.
Smooth, clump-free volume.
New Snapscara!
Only from Maybelline New York.
Now, eyeliner goes NYC-proof.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil
from Maybelline New York.
Smudge resistant.
Sweat resistant.
Waterproof.
Up to 36-hour wear.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil.
Only from Maybelline New York.
Every baby can have the freedom
to move their way In Pampers
Cruisers
with
three-way fit
They adapt at the waist, legs
and bottom
for all the freedom
to move their way
Pampers
New Tide PODS 2.0
with upgraded 4-in-1 technology.
Your detergent,
Stain removers,
And odor fighters
All fit, in the palm of your
hand.
#1 stain and odor fighter, #1
trusted.
It's got to be Tide.
♪
>>> 10:54.
WE TALKED A LOT ABOUT THE RECORD
INTERNET POST THE INSTAGRAM POST
OF THE EGG AND WHAT WAS THE DEAL
BEHIND IT BECAUSE IT WAS THE
MOST VIEWED INSTAGRAM POST EVER.
WELL, NOW WE KNOW A LITTLE BIT
MORE ABOUT THAT MYSTERIOUS EGG.
WHAT THAT ACCOUNT WAS ALL ABOUT.
IT'S REALLY ABOUT MENTAL HEALTH.
NOW THAT INITIAL POST SENT THE
INTERNET INTO A FRENZY AS A LOT
OF CURIOUS USERS TRIED TO FIGURE
OUT THE IDENTITY MYSTERIOUS EGG.
SO HULU PUT AN END TO ALL OF THE
QUESTIONS YESTERDAY IN A 302nd
EPISODE ENTITLE THE THE REVEAL
OF THE SHOW WORLD RECORD EGG.
NOW THEY DISCLOSED THAT THE EGG
ITSELF IS TIED TO MENTAL HEALTH
AWARENESS CAMPAIGN AND THEY DID
IT IN TRUE SUPER BOWL AD
FASHION.
ESSENTIALLY SOMETHING HULU DID
ABOUT SOCIAL, UM, MEDIA
AWARENESS WHEN IT COMES TO
MENTAL HEALTH.
AT THE START OF THE HE HAD SOAP
THE EGG SLIGHTLY CRACKED
INTRODUCES ITSELF AND NOTES
RECENTLY I STARTED TO CRACK.
THE PRESSURE OF SOCIAL MEDIA IS
GETTING TO ME.
THE EPISODE ENDS WITH F YOU'RE
STRUGGLING, TOO, TALK TO
SOMEONE.
DIRECTING VIEWERS THEN TO A
MENTAL HEALTH MANY WEBSITE.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> NOW WE KNOW.
>> INGENIOUS WHAT THE MYSTERY OF
THE EGG WAS ALL ABOUT.
>> IT'S COMPLICATED.
>> RIGHT.
>> A LOT GOING ON THERE.
>> THOUGHT THEY WERE JUST TRYING
TO UP STAGE CAN ILY JENNER.
WHO KNEW.
>> WORKED SO FAR.
RIGHT.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> WORKED SO FAR.
>> MAYBE WE CAN SHOW THE SEVEN
>> WHAT'S GOING ON.
DAY FORECAST.
>> MAYBE WE CAN SHOW THE SEVEN
60 TODAY.
DAY FORECAST.
DARE I SAY MAYBE A SPOT GETS TO
60 TODAY.
70 TOMORROW.
DARE I SAY MAYBE A SPOT GETS TO
>> OH, BOY.
70 TOMORROW.
>> I HAVE A TIP JAR OUTSIDE.
>> OH, BOY.
IT'S GOT MY FACE ON IT.
>> I HAVE A TIP JAR OUTSIDE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT'S GOT MY FACE ON IT.
>> WHY NOT?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> YEAH.
>> WHY NOT?
>> ANDREW JACKSON WILL BE
>> YEAH.
SEPTEMBERED.
>> ANDREW JACKSON WILL BE
66 TOMORROW BUT NOTICE ALL WEEK
SEPTEMBERED.
LONG WE KEEP IT WELL ABOVE
66 TOMORROW BUT NOTICE ALL WEEK
NORMAL.
LONG WE KEEP IT WELL ABOVE
WE WILL BE COOLER, COLD NEXT
NORMAL.
WEEKEND BUT TODAY 60 DEGREES.
WE WILL BE COOLER, COLD NEXT
SUNNY, BRIGHT, BEAUTIFUL AND D
WEEKEND BUT TODAY 60 DEGREES.
DRY.
SUNNY, BRIGHT, BEAUTIFUL AND D
>> I THINK EVERYBODY WILL BE
DRY.
VERY HAPPY.
>> I THINK EVERYBODY WILL BE
>> OH MY GOSH.
VERY HAPPY.
>> NICE RESPIT FROM WINTER.
>> OH MY GOSH.
>> AFTER LAST WEEK THIS IS A
>> NICE RESPIT FROM WINTER.
GREAT ONE.
>> AFTER LAST WEEK THIS IS A
>> MAUREEN, LEAD US TO THE
GREAT ONE.
CHOCOLATES.
>> MAUREEN, LEAD US TO THE
>> LET'S GO.
CHOCOLATES.
TRUFFLES FOR ALL.
>> LET'S GO.
I'M TELLING YOU ALL YOU NEED IS
TRUFFLES FOR ALL.
ONE PIECE AND YOU ARE DONE BUT
I'M TELLING YOU ALL YOU NEED IS
IT'S SO DELICIOUS.
ONE PIECE AND YOU ARE DONE BUT
>> THIS IS AMAZING.
IT'S SO DELICIOUS.
>> THIS IS NOT A BAD WAY TO END
>> THIS IS AMAZING.
A MONDAY, RIGHT?
>> THIS IS NOT A BAD WAY TO END
>> NO.
A MONDAY, RIGHT?
AW, MAN.
>> NO.
>> LET'S DIVE IN.
AW, MAN.
>> LOOK WHAT SHE DID.
>> LET'S DIVE IN.
SHE MADE THEM BEAUTIFUL.
>> LOOK WHAT SHE DID.
>> VERY DECADENT.
SHE MADE THEM BEAUTIFUL.
VERY HEALTHY FOR YOU.
>> VERY DECADENT.
WE'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
Switch to Fios and get
entertainment delivered
to your home like no one else.
Because Fios is a 100%
fiber-optic network.
That means you'll get the
fastest internet available
and Fios TV One with amazing
4K capability,
and an advanced voice remote.
And now we'll give you a Netflix
premium plan for a full year.
So you can stream your favorite
Netflix shows
and movies in 4K on 4
devices at once.
Already have Netflix?
We'll cover the cost for one
year.
Just switch for 79.99 a month
with a two-year agreement
and get Fios Gigabit Connection
with TV and phone
with a 2-year price guarantee.
And not only will you get a
Netflix premium plan on us for a
year,
you'll be able to find Netflix
in the Fios Channel guide
and use the advanced voice
remote to launch Netflix
and easily find all the
channels,movies and shows
you love.
When you think about it,
there are so many entertaining
reasons to switch to Fios.
100% fiber-optic network.
100% phenomenal.
Go to getfios.com today.
>> Announcer: LIVE FROM
NEW YORK CITY, IT'S
"THE WENDY WILLIAMS SHOW."