>>> GOOD MORNING AND WELCOME TO
GREAT DAY WASHINGTON.
CHRISTEN
IS OUT TODAY BUT IF YOU ARE AT
HOME AND LOOKING FOR A MATE
WE'VE GOT SOME GREAT DIGITAL
DATING TIP THIS IS MORNING PLUS
WE'RE SHARING HOW A GROUP OF
LOCAL SCIENTISTS ARE WORKING
HARD TO COMBAT POLLUTION.
FIRST
LET'S GET OVER TO WUSA 9
METEOROLOGIST HOWARD BERNSTEIN
FOR AN UPDATE ON THE FLASH FLOOD
WARNING WE'RE CURRENTLY
EXPERIENCING.
>>> WE'VE BEEN EXPERIENCING SOME
FLOODING RIGHT NOW.
THESE ARE
FLOOD WARNINGS FROM FREDERICK
INTO SOUTHERN GEORGE COUNTY.
THESE ARE THE WORST, MOST
DANGEROUS TYPE OF FLOODING AND
HAPPENS VERY QUICKLY.
IT ONLY
TAKES A FOOT, TWO FEET OF WATER
TO PUSH YOUR CAR OFF THE ROAD SO
THAT'S WHY YOU HEAR TURNED
AROUND, DON'T DROWN.
EVEN HOWARD
COUNTY UNDER A FLASH FLOOD
COUNTY UNTIL 11:45.
AND
MONTGOMERY SEEING SOME HEAVY
RAIN.
MERI AND I WERE LOOKING AT
SOME OF THE PRESIP INTENSITY IN
THE FIVE PLUS INCHES PER HOUR SO
THESE ARE TROPICAL DOWNPOURS
CAUSING SOME FLASH FLOODING, BUT
A NUMBER OF WATER RESCUES IN
FREDERICK AND MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
I-66 SOUTH SEEMS TO BE THE
HEAVIEST.
YOU'RE STARTING TO SEE
HEAVY RAIN MOVE IN AND
EVERYWHERE ORANGE AND RED, VERY,
VERY HEAVY RAINFALL FROM FedEx
FIELD ACROSS THE HEART OF D.C.
MOVING TOWARDS THE HEART OF
ALEXANDRIA.
OUR FRIENDS IN MT.
VERNON, AND PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY, GENERALLY SOUTH OF JOINT
BASE ANDREWS, GET READY AS THIS
WHOLE MASS OF WATER IS MOVING
TOWARDS YOU WITH THE FLASH FLOOD
WARNING UNTIL 11:15, AND WE'RE
GOING TO SEE BETTER WEATHER.
ONCE WE GET RID OF THE STUFF
THIS MORNING WE'LL SEE THE
ACTIVITY SHIFT OFF TO THE SOUTH
AND WEST AS WE GET INTO THE
AFTERNOON.
THE NEXT ONE TO TWO
HOURS COULD BE PARTICULARLY BAD
TWO FLOODING BUT IT WILL GET
BETTER THIS AFTERNOON.
>> I HOPE SO.
THIS IS A LIVE
LOOK AT THE BELTWAY.
WE HAD A
CLOSURE.
THEY JUST OPENED A 2
LEFT LANE ON THE INNER LOOP BY
THE AMERICAN LEGION BRIDGE.
THIS
HAS BEEN GOING ON FOR A WHILE.
IT SOUNDS LIKE THERE WAS A TREE
THAT FELL ON TO A VEHICLE AND
CAUSED SOME SORT OF ACCIDENT.
THEY'RE TRYING TO MOVE IT OVER
TO THE RIGHT HAND SIZE AS
QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
THAT'S THE
INNER LOOP OF THE BELTWAY,
COMING FROM THE SPRINGFIELD
INTERCHANGE.
I- 270, THE BELTWAY
IS NOT LOOKING GOOD, AND WE'VE
HAD MANY RISK YOUS UP IN
FREDERICK, AS WELL, FOLLOWING
FREDERICK COUNTY, THE POLICE
DEPARTMENT'S TWITTER PAGE.
THESE
ARE JUST THE MAIN STREETS, NOT
EVEN SIDE STREETS.
DEFINITELY
IMPACTING YOU AS YOU HEAD OUT
THE DOOR..
>>> THE U.S. WOMEN'S SOCCER TEAM
GOT QUITE THE WELCOME LAST NIGHT
WHEN THEY RETURNED TO THE HOTEL
IN FRANCE.
THE U.S. CAPTURED ITS
FOURTH WOMEN'S WORLD CUP TITLE
IN A 2-0 WIN OVER THE
NETHERLANDS.
CAPTAIN MEGAN
RAPINOE WAS NAILED OUTSTANDING
PLAYER AND DILL DE BLASIO
INVITED THEM TO A PARADE OF
HEROES ON WEDNESDAY.
>>> THERE WAS PANIC INSIDE UNION
STATION AFTER LOUD BANGS WERE
MISTAKEN FOR GUNSHOTS.
IT
APPEARS THIS WAS ALL JUST
FIREWORKS AND HAPPENED SHORTLY
BEFORE 5:00 AND MANY PEOPLE TOOK
TO SOCIAL MEDIA TO DOCUMENT THE
CHAOS.
ONE GUY SAID HE LOOKED
FOR EXIT SIGNS AND WALKED OUT
THE BACK OF THE STORE WITH OTHER
CUSTOMERS AND OTHERS SAY THEY
HID IN A RESTROOM UNTIL THEY
WERE GIVEN THE ALL CLEAR.
>> IT'S CRAZY WE LIVE IN A
SOCIETY, IN AMERICA AND ALL
ACROSS THE WORLD, WHEN WE HEAR
UNEXPECTED SOUNDS IT DRAWS OUR
ATTENTION TO WHAT, FORTUNATELY,
IT CAN BE.
IT'S JUST THE TIMES
WE LIVE IN.
YOU NEVER KNOW
ESPECIALLY AFTER 9/11.
YOU
REALLY NEVER KNOW WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN.
>> IT IS PANIC CAUSED A
STAMPEDE.
POLICE ARE
INVESTIGATING BUT WOULD NOT SAY
IF SOMEONE WAS ARRESTED.
HOWEVER
WITH ALL OF THOSE CAMERAS INSIDE
AND OUTSIDE, IT IS LIKELY THEY
KNOW HOW THIS WAS CARRIED OUT.
>>> AND JUST LAST WEEK,
FIREWORKS SPARKED A STAMPEDE AT
NAVY PIER IN CHICAGO.
A PRIVATE
SECURITY OFFICER TOOK THE SOUNDS
AS GUNFIRE AND SHOUTED FOR
EVERYONE TO TAKE COVER.
AT LEAST
13 PEOPLE WERE TAKEN TO THE
HOSPITAL.
>>> AND PICTURES OF A BOY
HELPING OUT THE HONOR GUARD IN
ARLINGTON, TEXAS, AT A PARADE
THAT WAS HELD IN THE CITY.
HIS
FELLOW OFFICERS ASKED JOSH TO
TIE THE SHOE.
HE WAS A LITTLE
BIT NERVOUS BUT GOT THE JOB
DONE.
THE NEXT DAY, THE OFFICER
THANKED HIM FOR HELPING OUT AND
HOPES TO BE A POLICE OFFICER
WHEN HE GROWS UP.
>>> THE BOARD OF ELECTIONS
AGREED TO LIST X AS A GENDER
OPTION ALONG WITH MALE, M, AND
FEMALE.
THAT LAW GOES INTO
EFFECT ON THE 1st.
>>> AND ASHLEY DARBY AND HER
HUSBAND, MICHAEL, WELCOMED A
BABY BOY.
SHE SAID SHE'S YET TO
REVEAL THE BABY BOY'S NAME AND
WE'RE ALL WAITING FOR THAT.
I
WAS HER MISS AMERICA ROOMMATE.
NEVER THOUGHT I'D GET TO
ANNOUNCE HER FIRST CHILD ON AIR.
CONGRATULATIONS, ASHLEY.
NOW
WE'LL SEND THINGS OUT , TO YOU.
>> Reporter: ORIGINALLY WE WERE
GOING TO BE OUT THERE TALKING.
THE PROVINCE, THAT OLD TALL SHIP
AT FOUNDER'S PARK.
THERE ARE SO
MANY WARNINGS AND WATCHES FOR
FLOODING IN THE AREA WE WANTED
TO SHOW YOU WHAT THINGS ARE LIKE
IN ALEXANDRIA.
RAIN IS COMING
DOWN IN BUCKETS AND MANY STREETS
ARE PRONE TO FLOODING ESPECIALLY
WHEN WE WERE IN THE FLASH FLOOD
SITUATION.
SO YOU CAN TELL THERE
IS NOBODY OUT HERE.
PEOPLE HAVE
GONE AHEAD AND FOUND SOME
SHELTER BUT IT IS CERTAINLY
COMING DOWN.
WE COULD JUST SEE
IT BEFORE IT GOT HERE, JUST THAT
DARK LINE CONTINUED TO MOVE
CLOSER AND CLOSER OVER THE LAST
30 MINUTES WHICH IS RIGHT HERE.
I'M GOING TO STEP IN FOR A
SECOND, DRY OFF A LITTLE BIT,
TRY AND GET THE DROPS OFF MY
HAT.
IN THE MEANTIME, BACK TO
YOU, LADIES, IN THE NICE, DRY
STUDIO.
>>> THE DATING SCENE IS TRUCKIER
THAN TRICKIER
THAN EVER.
COMING UP
>>> WELCOME BACK TO GREAT DAY
WASHINGTON.
WE'LL TELL YOU ABOUT
DIGITAL DATING WITH AN AUTHOR OF
A BOOK WHO WANTS TO SAVE FROM
SOME DIGITAL DISASTERS.
>> I WAS RESEARCHING WHEN DATING
APPS.
PEOPLE REALLY WANT
MEANINGFUL CONNECTIONS, AND SO
THIS IS THE ULTIMATE DATING
WELLNESS BOOK.
I WANT YOU TO BE
ABLE TO FIND LOVE.
>> AND PEOPLE ARE HAPPIER AND
HEALTHIER WHEN THEY DO HAVE A
MATE, BUT HOW DO YOU DO IT
NOWADAYS WHEN IT SEEMS LIKE
EVERYTHING STARTS OUT IN A
DIGITAL RELATIONSHIP.
YOU'RE NOT
MEETING PEOPLE FACE TO FACE
ANYMORE.
>> IT'S JUST SO HANDY.
ON A DAY
LIKE TODAY YOU WANT TO BE
INDOORS OR YOU'RE A SINGLE MOM,
WE LIKE TO DO EVERYTHING FROM
OUR PHONE.
WE NEED TO BE CAREFUL
HOW WE PUT OURSELVES ON THE
SINGLES MARKET.
THERE ARE SOME
THINGS I EXPLAINED TO HAVE A
MEANINGFUL CONNECTION.
>> SO TO DO THE RESEARCH YOU
WENT UNDERCOVER. WHAT DOES THAT
MEAN?
>> I DIDN'T TELL THEM WHO I WAS
AND HOW IT WAS TO NAVIGATE
THROUGH THE WORLD OF DIGITAL
DATING AND OTHER TIMES I'M JUST
AN AUTHOR AND RESEARCHING AND A
LOT OF PEOPLE WOULD YOU WOULD
REPLY BACK AND SOME TIME --
>> YEAH.
>> I SAID IT'S EASY, TELL ME
ABOUT YOUR EXPERIENCE.
AND THEY
SAID CAN WE BE ON A DATE AND I