.
>>> GOOD MORNING.
WELCOME TO GREAT DAY
WASHINGTON.
>>  TODAY WE FEATURE A MAN WHO
WENT FROM 400 POUNDS
TO LOSING SO MUCH HE LANDED ON
THE COVER OF WORLD'S
RUNNER'S MAGAZINE.
>>  IT'S AN INSPIRING JOURNEY.
>>  AND IMPORTANT FACTS ABOUT
CAR SEAT SAFETY.
WE HAVE HAD IT ALL IN THE NEWS.
WE HAVE ALL THE CAR SAFETY THAT
YOU NEED TO KNOW.
>>> THE COUNTRY THIS MORNING IS
REACTING TO THE
PRESIDENT'S SECOND STATE OF THE
UNION ADDRESS AFTER
LAST NIGHT THE PRESIDENT CALLED
FOR AN END TO THE
POLITICAL STALEMATE BETWEEN
REPUBLICANS AND
DEMOCRATS.
MATT GREGORY HAS MORE.
>> Reporter: HERE ARE THREE
THINGS TO KNOW FROM
THE STATE OF THE UNION AND THE
DEMOCRAT'S RESPONSE.
NUMBER ONE, THE PRESIDENT
CALLED FOR CONGRESS TO
PASS TIGHTER BORDER SECURITY
MEASURES.
THIS INCLUDED A CONTINUED CALL
FOR A BORDER WALL
BETWEEN THE UNITED STATES AND
MEXICO.
NUMBER TWO, THE PRESIDENT
REVEALED HE WILL HAVE
ANOTHER MEETING WITH NORTH
KOREA.
THE SUMMIT WILL HAPPEN FEBRUARY
27th AND 28th IN
VIETNAM AND THE GOAL IS TO GET
AN AGREEMENT FOR
DENUCLEARIZATION.
AND STACY ABHRA MS BLAMED THE
PRESIDENT FOR THE
COUNTRY BEING DIVIDED AND
POINTED TO THE 35 DAY
PARTIAL GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN AS
AN EXAMPLE OF HIS
REFUSAL TO COMPROMISE AND HOW
THAT HURT THE COUNTRY.
>>  AS MATT SAID ABHRAMS GAVE
THE DEMOCRATIC
RESPONSE AND BLAMED THE
SHUTDOWN ON THE PRESIDENT.
>>  THE SHUTDOWN WAS A STUNT.
ENGINEERED BY THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES.
ONE THAT ABANDONED OUR PEOPLE
AND OUR VALUES.
>>  SHE SAID THOUGH SHE
DISAGREES WITH THE PRESIDENT
SHE DOESN'T WANT HIM TO FAIL.
ONE OF THE PEOPLE IN THE HOUSE
CHAMBER FOR THE
SPEECH WAS A WOMAN WE FIRST MET
DURING THE SHUTDOWN.
SHE IS A FEDERAL CONTRACTOR
FURLOUGHED DURING THE
SHUTDOWN.
SHE AND OTHERS NEVER GOT BACK
PAY.
SHE ATTENDED THE ADDRESS AS A
GUEST OF A
CONGRESSWOMAN AND SHE HAD A
MESSAGE FOR THE
PRESIDENT.
>>  MR. TRUMP, PLEASE AT THIS
POINT, JUST GO HEAD
AND BUILD YOUR WALL.
YOU SAY YOU WAS GOING TO BUILD
IT.
YOU WAS GOING TO PAY FOR IT.
PAY FOR IT.
NANCY IS NOT GOING TO PAY FOR
THE WALL.
STOP HOLDING US HOSTAGE EVERY
TIME YOU GET A NOTE.
>>> ITS BEEN FIVE DAYS SINCE WE
LEARNED ABOUT THE
RACIST PHOTOGRAPH IN THE 1984
YEAR BOOK OF THE
VIRGINIA GOVERNOR.
THOUGH HE HASN'T BEEN SEEN IN
PUBLIC FOR DAYS HE IS
STILL SAYING HE WON'T RESIGN.
YESTERDAY HE GOT SOME SUPPORT
FROM HIS OLD
CLASSMATES.
NINE STUDENTS HAVE COME FORWARD
TO DEFEND THE
GOVERNOR.
THEY WERE ALL CLASSMATES OF HIS
AT EASTERN VIRGINIA
MEDICAL SCHOOL.
LET'S START THERE AND THEN TAKE
A LOOK AT WHAT THEY
WROTE.
>>  HERE WAS THE STATEMENT.
WE BELIEVE THE GOVERNOR IS
NEITHER OF THE
INDIVIDUALS IN THE COSTUMES.
WE ATTENDED CLASSES WITH HIM.
WE SOCIALIZED WITH HIM.
WE KNEW HIM VERY WELL.
YET, THINGS REMAIN ROCKY FOR
THE GOVERNOR.
HE HAS BEEN HELD UP IN THE
EXECUTIVE MANSION, HIS
CALENDAR NOT UPDATED FOR DAYS,
MANY PUBLIC EVENTS
CANCELED.
BEHIND CLOSED DOORS HE IS
TRYING TO GOVERN.
HE SIGNED OFF ON LEGISLATION TO
GIVE AMAZON MILLIONS
IN INCENTIVES AND SENT OUT A
STATEMENT OF SYMPATHY
TO THE FAMILY OF A STATE
TROOPER KILLED IN THE LINE
OF DUTY.
AT THIS POINT MANY LAWMAKERS
FROM BOTH PARTIES, ARE
CALLING FOR HIS RESIGNATION.
>>  I CAN'T TELL YOU WHY HE
HASN'T RESIGNED BUT I'M
PRAYING HE WILL DO THAT.
>>  WE HAVE CALLED FOR THE
RESIGNATION.
>> Reporter: ADDING TO THE
CRISIS, SEXUAL ASSAULT
ALLEGATIONS DATING BACK TO 2004
AGAINST THE
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR, JUSTIN
FAIRFAX.
>>  THE ALLEGATIONS VAPORIZED
FOR A YEAR AND ONLY
CAME BACK ON THE EVE OF
ELEVATION OF -- GIVEN THE
CURRENT SITUATION AND SO, IT'S
ALL POLITICAL.
IT'S A SMEAR.
>>  WE ARE LEARNING THAT THE
ACCUSER OF JUSTIN
FAIRFAX HAS HIRED A LAWYER AND
IT'S THE SAME LEGAL
TEAM THAT REPRESENTED THE BRETT
KAVANAUGH ACCUSER.
IF THE GOVERNOR WILL RESIGN,
THAT'S ANYONE'S GUESS.
>>  THANK YOU.
>>> EASTER SEALS HAS BEEN
MAKING PROFOUND POSITIVE
DIFFERENCES TO THE LIVES OF
CHILDREN AND FAMILY FOR
ALMOST A CENTURY.
WE VISITED PORTLAND, A 2-YEAR-
OLD WITH A RARE
DISORDER AT ONE OF EASTER SEALS
CHILD DEVELOPMENT
CENTERS.
SHE IS NOT ONLY GETTING THE
THERAPY SHE NEEDS TO
LEARN TO LIVE WITH HER
DISABILITY BUT SHE IS
THRIVING.
>>  ROUND.
WALL.
LOOK AT THAT.
>>  IT'S ARTS AND CRAFTS TIME
AT EASTER SEALS.
HERE AT THEIR NORTHEAST DC
CHILD DEVELOPMENT CENTER,
FLOWER AND WATER IS BEING
TURNED IN TO PLAYDOUGH.
>>  I WOULD LOVE TO HELP YOU.
>>  IT'S AN OPPORTUNITY TO BE
LIKE HER FRIENDS.
SHE HAS A VERY RARE SYNDROME.
>>  BASICALLY IT'S A LOT OF
DIFFERENT ISSUES.
FOR PORTLAND.
SHE HAS LOW TONE.
THAT KIND OF CAUSES HER TO HAVE
ISSUES WHEN THIS
COMES TO GROSS MOTOR SKILLS,
WALKING, TALKING, EVEN
BLADDER AND KIDNEY ISSUES
BECAUSE OF THE LOW TONE.
THEN WITH HER SHE HAS BALANCE
PROBLEMS.
>>  IT'S A NEW SYNDROME.
PORTLAND WAS JUST DIAGNOSED
LAST AUGUST.
FOR HER MOM, FINDING A DAYCARE
WHERE SHE COULD
THRIVE BECAME HER TOP PRIORITY.
>>  I WAS LOOKING FOR A
DAYCARE.
I WANTED SOMETHING THAT WAS
INCLUDING WHERE THEY HAD
SPECIAL NEEDS KIDS TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT MANY PLACES
AROUND THE CITY.
I ACTUALLY WAS RECOMMENDED THIS
PLACE.
WE CAME IN AND DID AN INTERVIEW
AND IT WAS LIKE LOVE
AT FIRST SIGHT.
>>  EASTER SEALS PROVIDES LIFE
CHANGING SERVICES FOR
PEOPLE WITH DISABILITIES.
IT'S ALL ABOUT HELPING
INDIVIDUALS ACHIEVE THEIR
POTENTIAL AND LIVE MEANINGFUL
LIVES EVERY DAY.
>>  EASTER SEALS PROVIDES A LOT
OF SUPPORT TO PEOPLE
THROUGHOUT THE SPECTRUM.
WE TAKE CARE OF CHILDREN WHO
ARE NORMALLY DEVELOPING
AND ABOUT 35% OF OUR KIDS ARE
RECEIVING AT LEAST ONE
THERAPY SERVICE.
>>  COME ON, PORTLAND, LET'S
GO.
>>  PORTLAND RECEIVED THERAPY,
INCLUDING PHYSICAL
AND SPEECH THERAPY.
>>  SOME HAVE INTELLECTUAL
DISABILITIES WHERE THEY
CAN'T HAVE THE SKILLS.
FOR PORTLAND, SHE SEEMS TO
UNDERSTAND, SHE SEEMS TO
KNOW WHAT IS GOING ON.
SHE IS TRYING TO VERBALIZE AND
COMMUNICATE TO OTHERS
WHAT IS GOING ON IN HER MIND.
>>  THAT IS WHERE HER SPEECH
THERAPIST COMES IN.
SHE IS BY PORTLAND'S SIDE ALL
DAY TO MAKE SURE SHE
DOESN'T MISS OUT ON ANY OF THE
FUN.
>>  WE ARE USING AN AAC DEVICE.
IT HELPS PORTLAND EXPRESS THE
LANGUAGE THAT IS
CHALLENGING HER VERBALLY.
IT'S REALLY FUN.
PORTLAND UNDERSTANDS SO MUCH.
>>  I THINK BECAUSE SHE IS IN A
CLASSROOM WITH
TYPICAL KIDS IT HELPS HER MEET
THE MILESTONES.
>>  FOR A CHILD LIKE PORTLAND
SHE HAS ONLY BEEN HERE
LIKE FIVE OR SIX MONTHS AND HAS
MADE SUCH GREAT
GAINS.
>>  LOOK INTO IT.
IT'S ONE OF THE SCHOOLS THAT IS
-- TO ME IT'S A GEM.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT IT EXISTED.
SO, BEING ABLE TO COME HERE AND
SEE WHAT THEY ARE
DOING IS GREAT.
>>  THERE IS A GREAT WAY FOR
YOU TO HELP FAMILIES
LIKE HER AND PORTLAND.
>>  JOINING US NOW IS AMY
PRESS.
SENIOR DIRECTOR OF MARKETING
AND COMMUNICATIONS FOR
EASTER SEALS.
WELCOME.
>>  THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME AND
THANK YOU FOR
SHARING PORTLAND'S STORY AND
HELPING YOUR VIEWERS
UNDERSTAND MORE ABOUT WHAT WE
ARE DOING.
>>  IN ADDITION TO THE DAYCARE
YOU HAVE SO MANY MORE
PROGRAMS THAT HELP FAMILIES
RIGHT HERE IN OUR AREA.
>>  A LOT OF PEOPLE DON'T KNOW
THAT WE HELP VETERANS
FIND EMPLOYMENT AND FIND MENTAL
HEALTH SERVICES.
WE HAVE ADULT DAYCARE, RESPITE
CARE.
WE HAVE -- I ENCOURAGE PEOPLE
TO GO TO E SEAL.ORG.
>>  YOU HELP FAMILY THAT MAYBE
CAN'T PAY OR CAN ONLY
PAY A LITTLE.
YOU HELP ALL OF THAT.
ALL OF THIS REQUIRES HELP FROM
US AS WELL.
YOU HAVE A GREAT EVENT COMING
UP NEXT THURSDAY THAT
PEOPLE CAN HELP WITH.
>>  YEAH.
OUR BRIGHT STARS EVENT.
I HAVE TO THANK MNT BANK AND
ALL OF OUR RESPONSIBLE
SORES THAT MAKE THIS EVENT
POSSIBLE.
THE FUNDS RAISED THROUGH THIS
EVENT THAT TAKES PLACE
AT THE ARENA WITH DISNEY ON
ICE.
IT GOES TO SUPPORT PORTLAND AND
HER FAMILY AND ALL
THE FAMILIES.
ANYONE WHO IS INTERESTED IN
JOINING US AND BUYING
TICKET DEAR S CAN GO TO BRIGHT
STARS.ORG.
>>  WHERE DO PEOPLE GO IF THEY
WANT MORE INFORMATION
TO DONATE AND TO JUST TAKE PART
IN THE GREAT
PROGRAMS YOU HAVE
I LOVE THAT YOU MENTION ADULT
DAYCARE AS WELL AS
DAYCARE FOR CHILDREN.
>>  YEAH.
OUR WEBSITE HAS ALL THE
DETAILS, E SEAL.ORG.
ACTUALLY A NEW PROGRAM THAT WE
JUST LAUNCHED A FEW
MONTHS AGO IS EMPLOYMENT
SERVICES FOR INDIVIDUALS
WITH DISABILITIES TO HELP THEM
FIND MEANINGFUL
EMPLOYMENT.
THERE IS SO MUCH THAT WE DO.
WE CAN'T TALK ABOUT IT ALL.
IF PEOPLE GO TO THE WEBSITE AND
LEARN MORE I'M SURE
THERE ARE WAYS WE CAN HELP MORE
OF THEM IN THE
COMMUNITY.
>>  WHAT'S IT LIKE WALKING
THROUGH THE HALLS AND
SEEING THESE KIDS DAY AFTER DAY
>>  IT'S THE BEST PART OF MY
JOB.
SEEING PORTLAND'S STORY AND
JUST -- YOU KNOW, BEING
ABLE TO RUN DOWN TO THE CHILD
DEVELOPMENT CENTER OR
ADULT DAY CENTERS AND SEE ALL
THE WONDERFUL THINGS
THAT ARE HAPPENING EVERY DAY.
IT FILLS MY HEART AND IT'S WHAT
MAKES ALL OF US WHO
WORK AT EASTER SEALS HAPPY.
>>  THANK YOU FOR YOUR SERVICE.
IT WAS GREAT TO SEE THE HAPPY
PARENTS AND CONFIDENT
ABOUT YOUR PROGRAM AND HER
DAUGHTER THERE DURING THE
DAY.
>>  IN ADDITION TO -- THE KIDS
HAVE A GREAT TIME.
WE ARE SUPPORTING THE ENTIRE
FAMILY.
>>  THANK YOU AND THANK YOU
EVERYTHING EASTER SEALS
DOES.
>>  ABSOLUTELY.
WE WILL BE BACK AFTER THIS.
>>  OUR NEXT GUEST WENT FROM
WEIGHING OVER
400 POUNDS TO THE COVER OF
RUNNERS WORLD MAGAZINE.
HIS INCREDIBLE WEIGHT LOSS
JOURNEY NEXT.
.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO GREAT DAY
WASHINGTON.
OUR NEXT GUEST ONCE WEIGHED 420
POUNDS BUT SOMETHING
HAPPENED THAT SPARKED HIS
WEIGHT LOSS JOURNEY
LEADING HIM TO THE COVER OF
RUNNER'S WORLD MAGAZINE
AND A HEALTHIER LIFE.
JOSH LIFE.
YOU LOOK INCREDIBLE.
>>  THANK YOU.
>>  I THINK A LOT OF PEOPLE --
IT'S -- YOU LOOSE THE
WEIGHT BUT IT'S THE KEEPING IT
OFF.
HOW DOES IT BEGIN FOR YOU
>>  YOU LOOSE THE WEIGHT AGAIN
AND AGAIN.
FOR THE 3rd OR 4th TIME IN MY
LIFE.
IT JUST WENT DOWN THE JOURNEY
OF DOING ABOUT IT.
JUST WENT DOWN THE PATH OF
DOING SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
A LOT OF THOSE THINGS I DID IN
THE BEGINNING WERE
THE WRONG THING TO DO.
THEY WERE CRITICAL IN GETTING
MY MOMENTUM STARTED.
>>  THE THINGS YOU DID THAT
DIDN'T WORK OR THAT
MAYBE WORKS FOR A SHORT TIME IS
ALL BUILT UP.
>>  IT'S -- THEY HAVE ALL BEEN
LESSONS ALONG THE
WAY.
THAT'S SOMETHING -- THE BIGGEST
WORD
OUR BOOK IS DO.
IT'S A VERY SIMPLE TWO LETTER
WORD.
IF IT'S WRONG OR RIGHT.
DO SOMETHING, LET'S GET THE
PROCESS STARTED.
START WHERE YOU ARE AND LET'S
START MOVING THE BALL.
>>  AND A LOT OF PEOPLE SAY
THEY WANT TO LOOSE THE
WEIGHT.
THEY WANT TO LOOSE THE WEIGHT.
IS THERE SOMETHING THAT WAS
JUST -- THAT KIND OF
PUSHED YOU OVER THE EDGE AND
GOT YOU REALLY GOING ON
THAT
>>  YEAH.
IN THE BEGINNING IT WAS JUST --
I WANTED TO LOOK
BETTER IN A SUIT.
I WAS EMBARRASSED ABOUT HOW I
WAS GOING TO NEED
TO -- I KNEW I WAS GOING TO
HAVE TO WEAR A SUIT AT
THE END OF 2011.
I DIDN'T -- I WAS SCARED TO
STUFF MY BIG FAT
SELFINTO A SUIT.
SO, THAT WAS WHAT HAPPENED IN
THE VERY BEGINNING.
THE THING THAT SORT OF
PROPELLED ME FORWARD, REALLY,
WAS MY FALLING IN LOVE WITH THE
PHYSICAL ASPECT OF
THIS WHOLE THING WHICH IS THE
RUNNING AND REALLY
SORT OF BUYING IN TO THE FACT
THAT I'M A BIPED.
THAT'S WHAT I'M MEANT TO ME.
THEN I FALL IN TO THE COMMUNITY
OF RUNNERS AND, ONCE
I WANTED TO BE A BETTER RUNNER,
AND SAW THAT AS A
MORE REAL VERSION OF MYSELF,
THE EATING AND ALL OF
THE OTHER THINGS THAT WERE
CHANGING IN MY LIFE WERE
MADE MUCH EASIER FOR ME.
>>  WHAT WOULD YOU SAY THOUGH
TO SOMEONE THAT
MAYBE -- YOU KNOW -- AT THAT
HEAVY OF A WEIGHT IT'S
GOT TO BE HARD TO RUN AND GET
GOING.
>>  TERRIBLE.
>>  SOMEONE WILL GET OUT THERE
BUT EVEN IF YOU ARE
GOING AROUND THE BLOCK BUT
THEIR BODY HURTS AND THEY
GET FRUSTRATED.
>>  SLOW DOWN, RELAX.
WE DON'T HAVE TO DO IT ALL
TODAY OR THIS WEEK OR
THIS MONTH.
WE WANT TO START WHERE WE ARE.
WE WANT TO MOVE OURSELVES
FORWARD.
THAT MAY MEAN WALKING A 30
MINUTE MILE RIGHT NOW.
THAT'S WHERE WE ARE.
EMBRACE IT BECAUSE THAT
CAPACITY IS GOING TO GET YOU
TO THE PROMISED LAND.
WE HAVE TO REALLY HONOR WHERE
WE ARE TODAY AND BE
WILLING TO ENGAGE THAT FOR WHAT
IT'S WORTH AND GROW
IT HARD AND MOVE IT.
THAT'S JUST SOMETHING THAT I
HAVE LEARNED IN THE
PROCESS AND THAT I HAVE
REPEATED OVER AND OVER.
>>  THEY SAY EXERCISE IS 20% OF
LOSING WEIGHT.
THE DIET IS THE 80%.
YOU WERE A MEAT EATER.
YOU ARE FROM LOUISIANA.
>>  GOSH.
YES.
>>  YOU HAD PLENTY OF KING
CAKE.
>>  CRAWFISH BOILS AND DEER
MEAT.
>>  HOW DO -- YOU ARE PLANT
BASED NOW.
>>  I'M 1000% PLANT BASED.
YOU MAKE THE TRANSITION SLOWLY.
IT WAS A RECKON IND AND A VERY
UNCOMFORTABLE ONE.
IT WAS A MATTER OF ME READING
THINGS AND LEARNING
ABOUT THINGS IN THIS WEIGHT
LOSS PROCESS THAT REALLY
STARTED TO HOLD TRUE.
IF I WAS BEING OBJECTIVE WITH
THE 30 DAY TESTS I WAS
GIVING.
I WAS USING MYSELF AS A GUINEA
PIG.
ONCE I LEARNED WHAT WAS ON THE
OTHER SIDE OF THIS,
THIS NUTRITIONAL CHANGE, THIS
CHANGE IN, THIS CHANGE
IN IDEA ABOUT DIET IT BECAME
EASIER FOR ME TO ACCEPT
IT.
I HAVE SEEN SO MUCH CHRONIC
DISEASE AND HEART
DISEASE IN MY FAMILY AND IN
FELLOW PEOPLE THAT ONCE
I SAW THAT CONNECTION BETWEEN
THOSE THINGS, IT FELT
IRRESPONSIBLE OF ME, NOT LIKE
GLUTTONY JUST LIKE I
WAS DISRESPECTING THE HONOR AND
THE MEMORY OF PEOPLE
I HAD -- THAT I KNOW HAVE DIED
OF THESE PREVENTABLE
DISEASES.
IT BECAME SO MUCH MORE ABOUT
THE TASTE OF THE FOOD.
I COULD COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND
WHY THINK OF DESSERTS
AS DELICIOUS.
>>  YOUR BOOK, PEOPLE CAN GET
IT FOR FREE AS A KINDL
DOWNLOAD, RIGHT
>>  SURE.
THAT WAS VERY IMPORTANT FOR MY
PARTNER AND MYSELF TO
GET IN INFORMATION.
THINGS I HAVE LEARNED THROUGH
BLOOD, SWEAT AND TEARS
OUT INTO THE WORLD THROUGH A
PACKAGE THAT IS FREE.
I KNOW THAT IT'S SUCH IMPORTANT
INFORMATION TO HAVE
THAT BARRIER, TO REMOVE THAT
BARRIER IN SOME
CAPACITY IS VERY IMPORTANT TO
US.
>>  YOU ARE AMAZING.
YOUR JOURNEY IS AMAZING.
THANK YOU FOR SHARING IT WITH
US AND HELPING OTHERS
TO LIVE THEIR BEST HEALTHY
LIFE.
WE WILL SEE YOU MAYBE ON SOME
MORE MAGAZINE COVERS
HERE IN THE FUTURE.
WE WILL SEE.
JOSH, THICK TO FIT IS THE BOOK.
WELL START HEALTH IS THE
WEBSITE.
TOMORROW WE ARE HIGHLIGHTING
THE IMPORTANCE OF
REGULAR CHECK UPS AS A PART OF
A HEALTHY LIFESTYLE
AS WELL.
WE ARE DOING THAT BY HOLDING A
FREE HEALTH EXPO AT
THE YMCA IN RESTON.
WE CALL IT IMPACT HEALTH
MATTERS.
WE ARE PARTNERING THE RESTON
HEART CENTER TO OFFER
BLOOD PRESSURE, BMI TESTS AND
ALL SORTS OF DEMOS
LIKE DIABETES EDUCATION, CPR,
AGAIN THE SCREENINGS
ARE ALL FREE BUT WE ASK THAT
YOU SIGN UP FOR THEM SO
WE KNOW YOU ARE COMING.
THERE WILL BE TWO SESSIONS.
7:00 A.M.
TO NOON AND THEN 2:00 P.M.
THROUGH 7:00.
PLEASE GO TO THE WEBSITE,
WUSA9.COM/HEALTH MATTERS
FOR MORE INFORMATION AND TO
REGISTER.
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU OUT THERE
TOMORROW.
.
>>> COMING UP WE ARE LEARNING
THE PROPER WAY TO
INSTALL A CAR SEAT.
TODAY'S INFORMATION MAY
.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO GREAT DAY
WASHINGTON.
THIS MORNING WE ARE EXPLORING
THE CORRECT WAY TO
INSTALL A CHILD SEAT INTO YOUR
CAR.
WE STILL SEE IT EVERY DAY WHERE
PEOPLE DON'T HAVE
THEIR CHILDREN IN CAR SEATS.
WE WILL TALK TO LARRY WALKER
WITH THE DC, DMV.
YOU WERE SHARING A STORY.
YOU STILL SEE PEOPLE WHO DON'T
USE THIS LIFE SAVING
TOOL.
>>  YES.
AS AN INSPECTOR, HERE AT THE
MOTOR VEHICLES,
INSPECTOR SAFETY I GET A LOT OF
PARENTS COME THROUGH
WITH NO RESTRAINTS FOR THE
KIDS.
WE HAVE -- RESOURCES WE TELL
THEM ABOUT WHERE THEY
CAN GET A SEAT.
ALSO, WE CHECK THE SEAT TO MAKE
SURE IT'S INSTALLED
PROPERLY.
IF IT IS IN THE CARP.
>>  AND RIGHT HERE, THIS IS ONE
OF THE MORE
VERSATILE CAR SEATS THAT YOU
HAVE.
THIS IS CALLED A CONVERTIBLE.
>>  IT'S A CONVERTIBLE.
>>  CAN WE TAKE THIS AND PUT IT
IN THE CAR.
I WANT YOU TO SHOW ME THE
PROPER WAY TO USE THIS CAR
SEAT.
>>  YES MA'AM.
>>  GREAT.
>>  ALL RIGHT.
SO, IT'S CONVERTIBLE SEAT.
USUALLY THIS SEAT IS
RECOMMENDED FOR A
YOUNGER CHILD.
THIS SEAT IS DESIGNED TO FACE
BOTH WAYS.
REAR FACING, AND FORWARD
FACING.
THE REAR FACING, THERE ARE
ADJUSTMENTS YOU HAVE TO
MAKE.
THIS HAS THE ADJUSTABLE BASE
HERE THAT YOU BRING
DOWN.
YOU MAKE SURE THE SEAT -- WILL
HAVE THE PROPER TILT.
IF YOU NOTICE, THE ROOM THAT
YOU LOOSE.
SO, I WILL HAVE TO HAVE THIS
SEAT.
>>  YOU WILL REMOVE THAT SEAT
UP
>>  YEAH.
SEE THIS CAN TAKE TWO PEOPLE TO
DO PROPERLY.
THERE'S A BOX HERE.
THAT'S ABOUT.
>>  JUST TAKE -- [INAUDIBLE]
OUT.
>>  OKAY.
>>  IF YOU NOTICE THE SEAT JUST
SETTLES DOWN.
IN REAR STATIONS, THE BABY
SHOULD HAVE A CERTAIN
AMOUNT OF [INAUDIBLE].
ESPECIALLY THE YOUNGER BABY
WITH NO NECK CONTROL.
YOU WANT TO KEEP THE HEAD BACK.
>>  THAT MAKES SENSE.
>>  THE TILT, THE ELEVATED FOOT
HERE.
ALLOWS THE BABY TO REST BACK.
NOW, THIS SEAT HERE.
>>  WE WILL COME BACK AND
FINISH THIS INSTALLATION.
I ALSO WANT TO GIVE YOU A HEADS
UP.
WE WILL HAVE INFORMATION ABOUT
A VOUCHER PROGRAM.
IF YOU CAN'T AFFORD A SEAT YOU
CAN MAKE SURE YOU GET
ONE.
THAT'S COMING UP AFTER THIS.
>>  OKAY.
>>> COMING UP WE ARE MAKING
BLACK TRUFFLE PASTA WITH
A CHEF FROM LUPE VERDE IN THE
KITCHEN.
>>  TEMPERATURES ARE ON THE
RISE.
WE ARE
When was the last time
you felt...
Free.
It's time to uncover
that feeling again.
With the compassion and
strength of a name...
Most accepted by top doctors
and specialists.
And the power of a card...
that opens doors in
all fifty states.
Giving you the freedom to love
to dream to dance
Like no one is watching.
CareFirst
Blue Cross Blue Shield.
Live fearless.
.
>>> WE ARE EXPECTING SHOWERS.
OTHERWISE STILL DEALING
TEMPERATURES ABOVE AVERAGE.
NEARLY 50 IN DC.
RIGHT NOW HERE IS WHAT IT LOOKS
LIKE IN THE NEXT FEW
HOURS.
THERE ARE LIGHT SHOWERS ACROSS
THE CUMBERLAND AND
ROMNEY AREA.
AS YOU APPROACH THE FIVE AND
6:00 P.M.
HOURS WE ARE
LOOKING AT LIGHT RAIN ACROSS
METRO DC.
MOST OF THE DAY IS DRY.
IT'S DURING THE EVENING THAT WE
ARE ANTICIPATING THE
LIGHT SHOWERS PUSHING IN.
EIGHT TONIGHT AROUND THE DINNER
HOUR, WE ARE STILL
LOOKING AT SOME RAIN ACROSS THE
AREA.
NOW, AS WE LOOK AT TOMORROW,
THERE WILL BE A SHOWER
CHANCE AND TEMPERATURES WILL
CLIMB TO THE UPPER 50'S
TO EVEN THE MID60'S.
FRIDAY WE KEEP THAT RAIN CHANCE
IN AS WELL.
TODAY, 49 TO 59 TO THE NORTHERN
SUBURBS.
AREAS SOUTH OF DC.
YOU WILL BE APPROACHING THE MID
TO UPPER 50'S AND
EVEN NEAR THE 60-DEGREE MARK IN
A FEW AREAS TOWARD
THE SOUTH.
SHOWERS PUSHING IN FOR YOU THIS
AFTERNOON.
FRIDAY WILL BE THE GAME
CHANGER.
WE HAVE A STRONG COLD FRONT
COMING IN.
TAKE A LOOK AT FRIDAY'S HIGHS.
60'S TO START.
LOOK AT THIS COLD AIR FROM THE
NORTHWEST.
TEMPERATURES WILL BEGIN TO FALL
BY FRIDAY AFTERNOON.
WE WILL FIND A MUCH COOLER
WEEKEND ON TAP ONCE THAT
COLDER AIR SETTLES IN.
IT'S INDEED STILL WINTER WITH A
HIGH OF 39 DEGREES
SATURDAY AND SUNDAY STILL COLD
AT 41 DEGREES.
WE ARE ALSO TRACKING THE
POSSIBILITY OF SOME WINTER
WEATHER TO MAKE ITS WAY BACK
IN.
BETWEEN MONDAY, TUESDAY AND
WEDNESDAY.
THOSE DAYS WE ARE LOOKING AT A
WINTER MIX AND THE
CHANCE TO GET THE SNOW AROUND
HERE BY WEDNESDAY.
THIS IS YOUR MONDAY AT FIVE.
RAIN OVER DC.
A WINTER MIX TOWARD LEESBURG,
AND FREDERICK.
WE ADVANCE TO MONDAY AFTERNOON
AND IT TRANSITIONS
OVER TO ALL RAIN FOR EVERYBODY.
TUESDAY INTO WEDNESDAY, WE
COULD SEE MORE SNOW AND
RAIN AND SNOW.
EVEN SOME FREEZING RAIN MIXING
INTO THE AREA.
THAT'S TUESDAY LATER IN THE
MORNING AND THEN TUESDAY
EVENING WE WILL SEE THAT OUT TO
THE WEST AS WELL.
A LOT OF INTERESTING WEATHER
COMING OUR WAY.
56 DEGREES TODAY.
WE WILL SEE TEMPERATURES UP TO
65 BY TUESDAY.
BY THURSDAY WITH SHOWERS, MORE
SHOWERS FRIDAY WITH
FALLING TEMPERATURES AND
TEMPERATURES IN THE 60'S.
WE ARE COOLER THIS WEEKEND.
UPPER 30'S.
LOW 40'S AND MONDAY AND TUESDAY
WE ARE LOOKING AT
THAT WINTER WEATHER COMING BACK
IN.
MARQUETTE.
>>> WE ARE LOOKING FORWARD TO
THAT VALENTINE'S DAY
FORECAST.
IF YOU ARE THINKING ABOUT SOME
ROMANTIC ITALIAN FOOD
FOR VALENTINE'S DAY CHECK OUT
LUPO VERDE ON 14th
AND KEY STREET.
I'M JOINED BY THE CHEF WHO IS
THE DIRECTOR OF ALL
THREE LOCATIONS.
WELCOME.
>>  THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>>  YOU ARE IN PALISADES.
YOU ARE ALSO ON THE DC
WATERFRONT.
>>  THE WHARF.
>>  THE MENU IS DIFFERENT AT
EACH LOCATION.
TELL ME WHAT YOU ARE MAKING
TODAY AND WHERE IT'S
FROM.
>>  LET ME TELL YOU.
I'M DOING GREEN -- ITS HOME
MADE.
EVERYTHING IS FROM SCRATCH.
YOU CAN SEE MY FACTORY.
--
>>  BEAUTIFUL.
YOU KNOW I THINK ALL OF US WHO
GREW UP IN THE 08'S
AND 90'S ON THE CANNED, FROZEN
FOOD, I CAN'T TAKE
MORE OF IT.
YOU HAVE THE FRESH INGREDIENTS.
>>  EVERYTHING FRESH.
>>  HOW DO YOU GET STARTED WITH
THIS
>>  LOOK AT THIS.
>>  THIS MAY COME FROM GROWING
UP WITH YOUR ITALIAN
GRANDMOTHER, RIGHT
>>  YEP.
>>  I'M SCARED.
>>  OLIVE OIL, BUTTER, A LITTLE
BIT OF BLACK PEPPER
WITH SALT.
SALT.
A LITTLE BIT OF WATER.
ALL RIGHT.
LOOK AT THIS.
>>  AMAZING.
>>  YOU SEA THE PASTA BOILING
IN THERE.
HOW LONG DO YOU BOIL IT
>>  JUST TWO MINUTES.
>>  TWO MINUTES AND YOU ARE
DONE.
>>  YES.
>>  IT'S SO FRESH. YOU CAN'T GO
WRONG WITH FRESH PASTA.
MY GOODNESS.
I DON'T WANT TO BREAK IT.
.
>>  TELL ME ABOUT THE FLAVOR IT
ADDS FROM THE PASTA.
>>  WONDERFUL BLACK TRUFFLE
FROM TUSCANY.
IT'S IN SEASON RIGHT NOW.
IT'S A WINTER BLACK TRUFFLE.
>>  BEAUTIFUL.
>>  GOOD FOR RISOTTO AND PASTA.
PROTEIN LIKE A BEEF STEAK.
>>  AND YOUR BEEF LASA GNA THAT
YOU HAVE HERE.
>>  WITH SHAVED BLACK PEPPER.
WE HAVE THE SALAD WITH CEASAR.
ORANGE AS WELL.
ON YOUR SCREEN YOU SEE THE BEEF
LASAGNA.
LOOK AT THAT.
>>  BEEF RAGU.
>>  THAT'S AMORE.
THEN YOU HAVE THE.
BIRATTA SALAD.
IT'S CREAMY INSIDE.
>>  YUM.
AND -- ORANGE AS WELL.
>>  BEAUTIFUL DISH.
NOW, GETTING BACK TO THE --
IT'S BOILED FOR TWO
MINUTES.
>>  MY GOSH.
ALL RIGHT.
>>  OKAY.
THEN YOU PUT IT IN THE PAN TO
FIRM IT UP OR ADD THE
FLAVOR
I'M GETTING AWA  FROM THAT.
THINGS ARE POPPING IN THE GREAT
DAY KITCHEN.
>>  ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
LOOK AT THIS.
COLOR.
FLAVOR, A LITTLE BIT OF BUTTER.
>>  ALL RIGHT.
I UNDERSTAND.
>>  AND THEN.
>>  WE HAVE TO WRAP.
>>  PLEASE.
DO IT FOR ME.
>>  HOW MUCH IS THAT LIKE A
HUNDRED DOLLARS
>>  A LOT.
A LOT.
>>  THERE YOU GO.
THERE YOU GO.
>>  $500.
>>  I DON'T THINK SO.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>  I DON'T THINK SO
>>> THEY SAY THAT A WAY TO A
WOMAN'S HEART IS
THROUGH HER STOMACH.
>>  LOOK AT THIS.
>>  WE WILL BE BACK WITH MORE
AFTER THIS.
I WILL STUFF MY FACE.
.
>>> COMING UP WE ARE LEARNING
THE PROPER WAY TO
INSTALL A CAR SEAT.
WE HAVE AN EXPERT THERE.
HE WILL JOIN US.
>>> AND A FEDERAL WORKER WHO
RELIED ON HER PASSION
FOR AFRICAN JEWELRY TO SUPPORT
HER THROUGH THE
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN HOW
.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO GREAT DAY
WASHINGTON.
WE ARE LEARNING THE PROPER WAY
TO INSTALL CAR SEATS
FOR THOSE KIDS OUT THERE.
WE HAVE LARRY WALKER HERE OF
THE DMV DC.
HE DOES THIS ALL DAY LONG.
WE ARE TALKED ABOUT THE COMMON
THINGS THAT YOU SEE.
IF I CAN GET MY PHOTOGRAPHER TO
MOVE IN HERE.
WE WILL TAKE A LOOK AT THAT
LABEL.
WHAT DO WE NEED TO KNOW ABOUT
THESE LABELS ON CAR
SEATS
>>  WHEN INSTALLING THIS
PARTICULAR SEAT.
IT'S A CONVERTIBLE.
IT CAN FACE BOTH WAYS.
DEPENDING ON THE CHILD'S WEIGHT
AND AGE, ONE
DIRECTION WILL BE INCORRECT.
IF YOU LOOK AT THE LABEL, ITS
CLEARLY MARKED AS TO
THE WEIGHT LIMIT, THE LOWEST
LIMIT, THE HIGHEST
LIMIT, REAR FACING, AND FOR
FORWARD FACING.
YOU HAVE THE SAME LABEL, AND
IT'S -- ALSO HAS THE
WEIGHT LIMIT AND THE MAXIMUM.
>>  THERE'S NO WIGGLE ROOM ON
THESE.
PEOPLE NEED TO ADHERE TO WHAT
THEY READ AND WHAT IS
ON THE LABEL.
>>  NOW, THE AVERAGE PERSON
PURCHASING THIS SEAT
WOULD ASSUME BY IT BEING REAR
FACING, FORWARD FACING
THAT THE BELT IS ALREADY SET
UP.
AS YOU SEE, THIS BELT HERE IS
IN FORWARD FACING.
>>  THIS CAN BE KIND OF
COMPLEX.
IS THIS WHY PEOPLE SHOULD COME
TO YOU
YOU WILL INSTALL IT BUT BEYOND
THAT, YOU TEACH
PEOPLE.
>>  YES, MA'AM.
WE ARE HERE TO BUILD PEOPLE'S
CONFIDENCE THAT
THEY -- THEY ARE SECURING THEIR
BABY PROPERLY.
>>  YOU ARE A FATHER.
>>  I AM.
WHEN I HAVE MY KIDS WE DIDN'T
HAVE ALL OF THIS
INSTRUCTION AND DIRECTION.
>>  THE BEST THING TO DO IS TO
-- YES, ADHERE TO
WHAT YOU SEE ON THE LABELS AND,
YOU KNOW, WE ARE
ALSO GOING TO TALK ABOUT
HARNESSES.
WE WILL LET LARRY START TO
STRAP THIS ONE IN.
FOLLOW ME REAL QUICK.
THERE'S A VOUCHER PROGRAM.
I WILL GET YOU UP TO SPEED ON
WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW
ABOUT THAT.
THEN, ALSO, A CERTIFICATE THAT
YOU CAN TAKE TO THE
HOSPITAL BEFORE YOU TAKE YOUR
BABY HOME SO ALL OF
THAT AND MUCH MORE COMING UP.
>>> OUR NEXT GUEST GREW UP
WATCHING HER MOTHER WORK
A FULL TIME JOB AS A PUBLIC
SCHOOL PRINCIPAL IN
ADDITION TO SEVERAL ODD JOBS IN
ORDER TO PROVIDE FOR
HER EIGHT CHILDREN.
FIVE OF THEM GROWN.
YOU SEE ON YOUR SCREEN.
THAT WAS THE INSPIRATION BEHIND
KENNY CLARK STARTING
A BOUTIQUE FASHION BUSINESS.
SHE BECAME A FINANCIAL LIFE
LINE DURING THE 35 DAY
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
WELCOME TO GREAT DAY
WASHINGTON.
>>  THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>>  YOUR COMPANY IS NAMED AFTER
YOUR MOTHER WHO
INSPIRED YOU IN SO MANY WAYS.
>>  YES.
IT IS.
SHE DID.
IT'S NAMED AFTER MY MOM MILDRED
YANCY.
SHE HAD EIGHT CHILDREN.
SHE WORKED AS A TEACHER AND
PRINCIPAL.
SHE ALSO WORKED AS A SEAMSTRESS
AND MADE CORNBREAD
AND SENT PEOPLE IN THE MARKET
TO SELL THE BREAD.
SHE ALWAYS TAUGHT US TO NEVER
RELY ON A NINE TO FIVE
JOB BUT HAVE MULTIPLE SOURCES
OF INCOME.
>>  ALL OF HER WONDERFUL,
MOTHERLY ADVICE CAME INTO
PLAY DURING THE RECENT SHUT
DOWN.
THOUGH YOU ARE A HIGH RANGING
EXECUTIVE IN THE
GOVERNMENT YOU HAD TO RELY ON
THE JEWELRY FOR A BIT.
>>  IT GAVE ME THE TIME I
NEEDED TO TALK TO MY
ARTISANS, GET NEW DESIGNS FROM
THEM.
GET PIECES SPED UP TO BRING IN
TO THE MARKET AND
CONTACT MY CUSTOMERS TO LET
THEM KNOW WHAT PIECES
WERE COMING.
>>  AND I MET YOU AT AN EVENT
WHERE YOU HAD YOUR
BOUTIQUE ITEMS ON DISPLAY.
>>  THAT'S CORRECT.
>>  LITTLE DID I KNOW THAT YOU
WOULD BE AFFECTED BY
THIS.
I APPRECIATE YOU BRINGING YOUR
BEAUTIFUL PIECES HERE
TODAY.
YOU BROUGHT MODELS TO SHOWCASE
WHAT THEY ARE ALL
ABOUT.
WE SEE THE FIRST MODELS.
>>  YES, MA'AM.
OUR FIRST MODEL IS QUINLEY.
THAT IS OUR GLITTERED BUTTON,
CAPE  NECKLACE.
THIS PIECE CAN BE WORN CASUALLY
OR UPSCALE,
ELEGANTLY FOR AN EVENING OUT.
YOU CAN KICK OUT THE HIGH HEELS
AND THROW ON THE
SNEAKERS AND RUN AROUND TOWN
WITH THAT PIECE ON.
THIS IS A BEAUTIFUL PIECE THAT
WAS HANDCRAFTED IN
GHANA BY A SKILLED ARTISAN.
WE CURAT, PIECES FROM ALL ROUND
AFRICA.
HELPINGWOMEN AROUND THE WORLD
EDUCATE AND SUPPORT
THEIR FAMILIES.
>>  THERE'S ANOTHER MODEL
COMING OUT.
THE NEXT ONE IS SHOWCASING OUR
EVER POPULAR GOLD
BEADED BODY CHAIN.
THIS BODY CHAIN CAN BE AGAIN,
WORN CASUALLY OR
DRESSED UP WITH THE ELEGANT
BALL ROOM GOWN FOR AN
EVENING OUT.
SHOWCASING -- IT HAS A LITTLE
KEYHOLE IN THE BACK.
THAT IS HOUR GOLD BEADED BODY
CHAIN.
>>  SO UNIQUE.
BREATHTAKING.
YOU HAVE ONE LAST MODEL.
>>  ONE LAST MODEL IS CONNIE.
SHE IS WEARING OUR LARGE, CAPE
WEB.
THIS PIECE CAN BE WORN AS A
NECKLACE.
YOU CAN TWIST IT SO THAT THE
LONG SIDE IN THE FRONT
AND THE BACK AND THE TIE ON THE
SIDE.
YOU CAN TAKE IT OFF YOUR NECK
AND WEAR IT AROUND
YOUR WAIST AS AN OVER THE TOP
FOR YOUR PANTS OR A
DENIM OR WHATEVER YOU ARE
WEARING.
VERY VERSATIL, PIECE AND THE
PIECES WE ARE WEARING
ARE PART OF OUR OFFICE LINE
WHICH IS PRETTY
PROFESSIONAL PIECES YOU CAN
WEAR IN THE OFFICE OR
OUT ON THE TOWN AS WELL.
>>  STUNNING.
COMPLETELY STUNNING.
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE ALL THREE
AGAIN.
IF YOU COULD STEP TOWARD THE
CENTER.
I WANT TO GO BACK TO YOUR
MOTHER AS THEY ARE WALKING
TOWARD THE CENTER.
AMERICAN HEART MONTH IS IN
FEBRUARY AND THIS IS A
VERY SPECIAL TIME FOR YOU IN
HONORING YOUR MOTHER.
>>  YES.
MY MOTHER DIED OF BREAST CANCER
AND HEART FAILURE.
IT'S IN THAT VEIN THAT I FELT
THE NEED WITH ALLst
ADVICE SHE GAVE ME TO GO HEAD
AND DO SOMETHING TO
HONOR HER LEGACY.
SO, I ENCOURAGE EVERYBODY TO
TAKE CONTROL OF THEIR
HEALTH, TO TRY TO EXERCISE AS
MUCH AS WE CAN, EAT
PROPERLY AND MAKE CERTAIN THAT
WE ARE AWARE OF OUR
HEALTH ISSUES.
MOST ESPECIALLY, TAKE CARE OF
YOUR HEART.
>>  YOU HAVE INSPIRED ME IN SO
MANY WAYS THIS IN
SHORT TIME.
WHERE CAN WE FIND OUT MORE
INFORMATION ABOUT YOU
I UNDERSTAND YOU HAVE A POP UP
SHOPPING EVENT ON
FEBRUARY 16th.
>>  YES.
WE ARE OPENING UP OUR SHOWROOM
IN SILVER SPRING
MARYLAND.
WE WILL HAVE THE EVENT ON EVENT
BRIGHT.
IT'LL BE FROM TWO TO SIX WHERE
EVERYBODY CAN COME IN
AND SHOP.
>>  THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THE WEBSITE ON SOCIAL MEDIA, AT
MILLIE'S
INTERNATIONAL.
WE WILL BE BACK.
>>> FEBRUARY IS NATIONAL CANNED
FOOD MONTH.
WE GET THE MEAL INSPIRATION
RIGHT FROM YOUR PANTRY.
.
>>> APPROXIMATELY 75% OF
AMERICANS ARE NOT EATING
THE RECOMMENDS AMOUNT OF FRUITS
AND VEGETABLES.
HERE WITH TIPS ON HOW YOU CAN
GET  GOOD DISHES FROM
YOUR PANTRY IS TOBY.
WELL TO GREAT DAY.
>>  THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>>  FEBRUARY IS NATIONAL CANNED
FOOD MONTH.
YOU THINK OF CANNED FOOD.
HOW CAN WE USE THOSE TO PUT
GOOD FOOD ON OUR TABLE
>>  WHEN YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
INGREDIENTS ON HAND IT'S
EASY TO WHIP UP A CREATIVE,
DELICIOUS, HEALTHY MEAL.
ESPECIALLY DURING THE BUSY
WORKWEEKS THAT YOU CAN
FEEL GOOD ABOUT SERVING FAMILY
AND FRIENDS.
LISTEN TO THIS.
A WELL STOCKED PANTRY FULL OF
CANNED FRUIT AND
VEGETABLES CAN HELP YOU SERVE
UP THE RECOMMENDED 42
CUPS OF FRUIT AND 53 CUPS OF
VEGETABLES A FAMILY OF
FOUR NEEDS EVERY WEEK.
>>  WE HEAR ALL THE TIME TO
SHOP ON THE OUTSIDE OF A
GROCERY STORE.
WITH THESE CANNED FOODS HOW
DOES THEIR VALUE COMPARE
TO THE FRESH FRUITS AND
VEGETABLES WE GET IN THE
PRODUCE SECTION
>>  SOME CANNED FOOD HAVE EQUAL
IF NOT BETTER
PROFILES COMPARED TO THEIR
FRESH AND FROZEN
COUNTERPARTS.
THAT'S BECAUSE FRUIT AND
VEGETABLES ARE HARVESTED AT
THEIR PEAK OF RIPENESS AND THEN
WITH IN FOUR HOURS
THEY ARE CANNED WHICH LOCKS IN
THEIR NUTRITION,
THEIR FLAVOR AND THEIR
DELICIOUSNESS.
ANY TIME OF YEAR YOU WANT FRUIT
OR VEGETABLES,
WHETHER IN SEASON OR NOT YOU
HAVE FULL ACCESS TO IT
WITHOUT ANY ADDITIVES OR
PRESERVIAIVES.
>>  I LOVE IF YOU DON'T HAVE
TIME TO GO TO THE STORE
YOU SHOULD KEEP THOSE STOCKED
JUST IN CASE YOU NEED
SOMETHING GOOD.
WHAT EXAMPLES CAN YOU SHOW US
>>  ASSOCIATION I HAVE A LOT OF
YUMMY DISHES.
I WILL SHOW YOU WHAT MY  KID
LOVE.
I SERVE THIS CHICKEN AND
VEGETABLE SALAD.
YOU OPEN UP YOUR FRIDGE AND YOU
ARE READY TO COOK
AND ALL THE SUDDEN IT'S SPOILED
AND YOU HAVE TO
THROW IT OUT AND YOU FEEL
HORRIBLE
SO THIS IS WHERE THIS COMES IN.
I USE CANNED STRING BEANS AND
DICED TOMATOES.
I DON'T HAVE TO BUY AS MUCH SO
I THROW OUT LESS.
>>  AND IT'S ALL RIGHT THERE.
WHAT WOULD YOU SAY WE SHOULD
HAVE IN OUR PANTRY
WHAT ARE THE ESSENTIALS YOU
SUGGEST WE ALWAYS HAVE
>>  I LIKE TO RECOMMEND A
PROTEIN FOR EXAMPLE.
SO, LIKE SALMON, TUNA OR
CHICKEN.
FRUITS OR VEGETABLES.
PEACHES, TOMATOES AND ALL TYPES
OF BEANS.
ACCORDING TO A RECENT STUDY
KIDS AND ADULTS WHO USE
SIX OR MORE CANNED FRUITS PER
WEEK ARE MORE LIKELY
TO HAVE DIETS HIGHER IN 17
ESSENTIAL NUTRIENTS .
>>  THANK YOU FOR REMINDING US
THAT WE HAVE THAT
HEALTHY FOOD RIGHT THERE IN THE
PANTRY AND REWORKING
THE WAY OUR BRAIN THINKS ABOUT
CANNED FOOD.
REAL QUICK, WHERE CAN PEOPLE
GET MORE INFORMATION
>>  GO TO CANS GET YOU
COOKING.COM FOR A TON OF
DELICIOUS RECIPES.
>>  THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE APPRECIATE YOU BEING WITH
US.
WE WILL BE BACK WITH MORE RIGHT
AFTER THIS.
>>> THERE ARE WORKSHOPS.
COMING UP DID YOU KNOW THERE
ARE WORKSHOPS TO TEACH
YOU HOW TO PROPERLY INSTALL A
CAR SEAT
WE WILL TELL YOU HOW YOU CAN
.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO GREAT DAY
WASHINGTON.
ON THE HEELS OF SEVERAL
ACCIDENTS WHERE CHILDREN
WERE HURT OR KILLED AFTER BEING
EJECTED FROM CARS,
WE HEAD BACK OUT TO WRAP UP OUR
CAR SEAT
INSTALLATION.
>>  IT'S ALWAYS GOOD TO HAVE A
GREAT REMINDER.
WHAT OTHER THINGS CAN YOU GIVE
US TO KEEP OUR KIDS
SAFE
>>  I WILL TELL YOU WHAT.
HERE IS WHAT WE ARE LEARNING
TODAY.
WHAT PERSONALLY I'M LEARNING IS
THERE'S A LOT THAT
GOES INTO PROPERLY INSTALLING A
CHILD'S CAR SEAT.
THERE ARE RESOURCES LIKE LARRY
WALKER OVER HERE TO
NOT ONLY INSTALL IT FOR YOU BUT
SHOW YOU HOW TO DO
SO IN THE FUTURE.
THERE'S ALSO WORKSHOPS.
WE HAVE KAREN TO TALK ABOUT
THAT.
YOU GUYS WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT
WE DO WHAT HE WITH
CAN TO HELP KEEP OUR KIDS SAFE.
>>  WE OFFER TWO WORKSHOPS A
MONTH.
ONE ON THE SECOND TUESDAY OF
EVERY MONTH.
THE SECOND ONE IS AT TRUSTED
HEALTH ON MINNESOTA
AVENUE.
THE 4th THURSDAY OF EVERY
MONTH.
>>  WHAT NEW PARENTS MAY NOT
REALIZE IS THAT BEFORE
THEY EVEN CAN BRING THEIR CHILD
HOME FROM THE
HOSPITAL, WHAT DO THEY NEED
>>  THEY NEED TO HAVE THEIR CAR
SEAT PROPERLY
INSTALLED.
WE ALSO OFFER A CERTIFICATE TO
PROVE THEIR CAR SET
HAS BEEN PROPERLY INSTALLED.
>>  AND THE VOUCHERS.
THIS IS FOR PEOPLE WHO MAY NOT
BE ABLE TO AFFORD A
CAR SEAT BUT THEY CAN GET ONE
WITH YOUR HELP.
>>  IF YOU LIVE IN THE DISTRICT
OF COLUMBIA AND YOU
ARE A RESIDENT AND CAN PROVE
THAT WE OFFER YOU A
FREE VOUCHER, ONE FREE SEAT.
YOU REDEEM A VOUCHER AT ONE OF
THE LOCATIONS.
ONE IN PV, TRAFFIC DIVISION AND
THE OTHERS DC
INFORMATION STATION WHERE WE
ARE NOW.
YOU CAN GET THE VOUCHER FROM
THE DISTRICT OF
TRANSPORTATION.
>>  LOOK AT YOU RATTLING ALL
THAT OFF.
THIS CAN BE A COMPLEX.
THERE IS HELP OUT THERE.
MAKE SURE YOU GET THAT.
BACK TO YOU.
>>  THAT'S GREAT.
DITTO ON THAT.
I APPRECIATE THE AWARENESS.
I HOPE WE SAVE A LIFE TODAY.
I WAS READING ABOUT FIVE
CHILDREN IN AN ACCIDENT.
IT'S THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
MAKE IT A GREAT DAY EVERYBODY.