.
>>> GOOD MORNING.
WELCOME TO GREAT DAY
WASHINGTON.
>>  TODAY WE MEET A LOCAL WOMAN
WHO IS A CONTESTANT
ON THE 38th SEASON OF SURVIVOR.
>>  WE GET THE LOW DOWN FROM
HER.
FIRST LET'S LOOK AT THE WINTER
WEATHER THAT'S COMING
IN TOMORROW.
MARY, WHAT'S THE LATEST
>>  GOOD MORNING.
YES, THIS WILL BE A SIGNIFICANT
WINTER STORM THAT'S
COMING OUR WAY, PRODUCING THREE
TO SIX INCHES OF
SNOW AND SLEET COMBINED OVER
METRO DC.
ALL THESE AREAS YOU SEE IN
WHITE IN THE
NEIGHBORHOODS.
SILVER SPRING, COLLEGE PARK,
THREE TO SIX INCHES
POSSIBLE, DOWN THROUGH THE
FREDRICKSBURG AREA.
HIGHER AMOUNTS NORTH AND WEST
OF DC ALONG FRONT
ROYAL, WINCHESTER AND
WESTMINISTER.
SIX TO EIGHT INCHES OF SNOW AND
EVEN SLEET COMBINED
IN THOSE AREAS WITH THE WINTER
WEATHER THREAT THAT'S
COMING IN.
WHAT TIME IS IT ALL GOING TO
START IN BETWEEN FOUR
AND FIVE FOR THE WINCHESTER AND
THE MARTINSBURG
AREA.
ALL THE AREAS IN BLUE.
BETWEEN SIX AND 7:00 A.M.
BETWEEN EASTON AREA.
LET'S TALK ABOUT WHAT YOU WILL
SEE.
AROUND THIS TIME TOMORROW SOME
MODERATE TO HEAVY
SNOW WILL BE FALLING AT THIS
POINT.
BY THE AFTERNOON, WE START TO
SEE THE WARMER AIR
COME IN.
THAT'S WHEN IT GETS
COMPLICATED.
WE WILL SEE A MIX CHANGE OVER
TO MOSTLY RAIN IN DC,
ANDREWS, BY TOMORROW EVENING'S
COMMUTE.
WHEN YOU ARE ALONG THE LEESBURG
AND FREDERICK AREA
THAT WILL HANG LONGER, CAUSING
A RISK FOR MORE ICE
TO FORM.
WE WOULD BE HAVING FREEZING
RAIN AND SLEET AND THAT
FREEZING RAIN COULD CAUSE
PROBLEMS ACCUMULATING
ENTREES AND POWER LINES WHICH
COULD ALSO LEAD TO
POWER OUTAGES.
HERE IS HOW MUCH ICE WE COULD
SEE.
UP TO A TENTH OF AN INCH AND
TWO TENTHS OF AN INCH
ALONG LEESBURG.
WE HAVE A WINTER STORM WARNING
IN EFFECT FOR THE DC
METRO AREA STARTING AROUND 1:00
A.M.
ENDING AT
7:00 TOMORROW EVENING.
COME UP IN THE NEXT UPDATE IN
ABOUT 20 MINUTES WE
WILL GO THROUGH THE STORM, GO
THROUGH EVERY COUNTY
TO LET YOU KNOW WHAT YOU CAN
EXPECT.
>>  WE WILL BE HERE EARLY
TOMORROW TO TRACK THIS FOR
YOU.
WAKE UP WASHINGTON STARTS AT
4:00 A.M.
>>> SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS SAYS
HE IS GIVING IT
ANOTHER AGO AND IS RUNNING FOR
THE DEMOCRATIC
NOMINATION FOR PRESIDENT IN
2020.
>>> MARYLAND AND VIRGINIA HAVE
JOINED IN THE FIGHT
TO STOP A SOUTHERN BORDER WALL
FROM BEING BUILT.
THEY JOINED A 16 STATE LAWSUIT.
MATT GREGORY HAS MORE ON WHY
THEY DECIDED TO SIGN
ON.
>> Reporter: THE NATIONAL
EMERGENCY ANNOUNCEMENT
GIVES THE PRESIDENT POWER TO
MOVE FUNDS AROUND
WITHOUT CONGRESSIONAL
APPROVALN.
THIS CASE THAT'S TO
PAY FOR THE BORDER WALL.
SIX BILLION DOLLARS WILL COME
FROM THE MILITARY
BUDGET.
IN VIRGINIA THAT THREATENS $131
MILLION IN MILITARY
CONSTRUCTION PROJECTS.
MONEY MEANT FOR SIX BASES.
MARYLAND COULD LOOSE $513
MILLION IN PROJECTS.
PROJECTS AT JOINT BASE ANDREWS.
THAT'S WHY MONDAY NIGHT BOTH
STATES SIGNED ONTO BE
PART OF A 16 STATE LAWSUIT.
>>  THE LAWSUIT WAS FILED ON
THE BASIS THAT THE
SITUATION AT THE BORDER IS NOT
AN EMERGENCY.
THIS IS WHAT THE COURTS WILL
HAVE TO DEFINE.
>>> THE DEPUTY ATTORNEY GENERAL
IS EXPECTED TO LEAVE
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT IN
MIDMARCH.
HISTHE DEPUTY ATTORNEY GENERAL
SAID IN JANUARY THAT HE
WOULD LEAVE SHORTLY AFTER A NEW
ATTORNEY GENERAL WAS
IN PLACE AND LAST WEEK WILLIAM
BARR WAS CONFIRMED AS
THE NEW ATTORNEY GENERAL BY THE
SENATE.
>>> THE VIRGINIA GOVERNOR IS
SET TO MAKE HIS FIRST
APPEARANCE RELATED TO HIS BLACK
FACE SCANDAL.
A PICTURE OF A PERSON IN BLACK
FACE AND ANOTHER
PERSON WEARING A KKK OUTFIT
APPEARED ON HIS YEAR
BOOK.
HE SAID IT WASN'T HIM IN THE
PHOTOGRAPH BUT DID
ADMIT TO WEARING BLACK FACE IN
THE PAST.
IS HE SET TO TRAVEL TO VIRGINIA
UNION UNIVERSITY.
ONE OF THE OLDEST BLACK
UNIVERSITIES IN THE SOUTH.
HE WILL BE THERE FOR A
CONVERSATION ABOUT RACIAL
INJUSTICE.
HE IS NOT SCHEDULED TO SPEAK.
>>> YOU WILL NOTICE SOME MORENO
MORE NO RED TURN ON RED
LIGHT SIGNS.
SOME  GO UP TODAY.
ITS PART OF THE MAYOR'S VISION
ZERO INITIATIVE THAT
AIMS TO STOP TRAFFIC RELATED
DEATHS BY 2024.
>>> FOR THE SECOND STRAIGHT
YEAR TEACHERS IN
WEST VIRGINIA WILL GO ON STRIKE
TODAY.
THEY ARE PROTESTING A BILL THEY
SEE AS REVENGE FOR
THEIR WALK OUT THAT LED TO A 5%
PAY RAISE.
A NEW BILL ALLOWS FOR CHARTER
SCHOOLS TO HELP
PARENTS PAY FOR PRIVATE
SCHOOLS.
BACK TO YOU.
>>  THANK YOU.
>>> THE 38th SEASON OF SURVIVOR
STARTS TOMORROW.
>>  THIS SEASON ONCE SOMEONE IS
VOTED OFF THEY HAVE
A CHANCE TO RETURN AND THEY
DON'T EVEN KNOW IT.
IT TESTS THEM ON HOW FAR THEY
WILL GO TO PLAY THE
GAME.
>>  THERE ARE TWO LOCAL
CONTESTANTS FROM THE AREA
AND WE HAVE A PEEK OF ONE RIGHT
NOW.
>>  WHAT MAKES ME UNIQUE
I WAS AT A WEDDING ONCE WITH
FIVE OTHER PEOPLE WITH
MY NAME.
YOU KNOW WHAT -- I TEND TO
TRUST PEOPLE.
I DON'T TEND -- TAKE THAT BACK.
I REALLY DON'T TRUST ANYONE.
IF YOU GO IN WITH LIKE ALL THE
STRATEGY YOU ARE OUT.
PEOPLE SEE THAT.
THEY KNOW THAT.
YOU CAN'T GO IN LIKE THAT.
YOU CAN'T GO IN SEARCHING FOR
AN IDOL BECAUSE YOU
ARE OUT.
YOU CAN'T GO IN SAYING I'M THE
MASTERMIND.
MY STRATEGY IS DON'T GET VOTED
OUT.
>>  I LOVE HER AND ONE OF THE
REASONS I LIKE HERE IS
SHE IS OLD ENOUGH TO NOT CARE
WHAT YOU THINK ABOUT
HER BUT SHE DOESN'T HAVE AN
EDGE BECAUSE OF IT.
SHE JUST DOESN'T CARE.
>>  SOME OF MY NOTES TO SELF.
WALK AWAY, DON'T SAY IT, GIVE
IT A MINUTE.
PATIENCE IS A GIFT.
I HAVE NOT BEEN HONORED WITH
THAT GIFT.
>>  JOIN
>>  I LOVE WATCHING THAT.
>>  CORRECT.
>>  TAKE YOU BACK TO ALL THE
FUN AND EXCITEMENT YOU
HAD.
>>  YOU KNOW WHAT
THERE'S NO REASON TO TRY TO ACT
LIKE SOMETHING YOU
AREN'T.
THAT'S ME.
THERE YOU HAVE IT.
>>  YOU KNOW A LOT OF PEOPLE
SAY YOU HAVE A LOT
GOING FOR YOURSELF.
YOU LIVE IN A GREAT AREA, YOU
HAVE KIDS, AND A GOOD
JOB IN SALES.
WHY DO YOU WANT TO GO ON THIS
SHOW
>>  IT'S A -- I GUESS IT WAS
LIKE A BUCKET LIST.
YOU SIT THERE AND YOU TALK ON
THE COUCH WITH YOUR
SPOUSE OR WHOEVER YOU ARE
WATCHING IT WITH AND ARE
LIKE WHAT ARE THEY DOING
I COULD DO THAT.
I WOULD HAVE DONE THAT.
WHY DID HE SAY THAT
YOU CAN TALK ABOUT HOW GREAT
YOU ARE OR YOU CAN
ACTUALLY APPLY.
IT WAS A PERFECT TIME.
I WAS ON A MOTHER'S DAY WEEKEND
WITH SOME OF MY BEST
FRIENDS.
I WAS DRIVING AND I -- I TOLD
MY BEST FRIEND.
I'M LIKE ROLL TAPE.
LET'S GO.
IT WAS CRAZY.
I DIDN'T EXPECT WHAT WAS COMING
OUT OF MY MOUTH.
IT WAS A LIKE A RANGE OF
EMOTIONS AND WE SUBMITTED
TO THE TAPE TO THE WRONG
WEBSITE.
IT WAS.
>>  LIKE THE AMAZING RACE
>>  THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN GREAT,
IF YOU ARE TED I'M
IN.
IT WAS JUST COME TO -- LIKE HOW
YOU GET SCHOOL
FOOLED BY SUBMIT HERE AND IT
WAS A TALENT AGENCY.
THEY DID CALL WHICH WAS GREAT
BUT THEY WANTED LIKE
$500 AND HEAD SHOTS AND I'M
LIKE NOPE.
THEN THEY CALLED AND IT WAS
GREAT.
>>  WAS IT EVERYTHING YOU
IMAGINED
YOU SIT THERE AND I CAN DO THAT
BETTER.
WHEN YOU GET THERE IN IT WHAT
WAS SOME OF THE
BIGGEST SURPRIS
>>  IT'S REAL.
IF MY -- I COULDN'T SAY
ANYTHING BUT REALITY TV IS
FAKE, SURVIVOR ISN'T REAL.
IT'S REAL.
>>  IT'S REAL.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU KIND OF
FORGET EVERYTHING THAT YOU
SAID WHEN YOU ARE ON THE COUCH,
WHEN YOU ARE IN THE
GAME.
IF SOMEONE IS -- GOING TO GET
ON YOUR NERVES,
SOMEONE IS GOING TO GET ON YOUR
NERVES.
YOU TRY TO BE QUIET BUT THINGS
HAPPEN.
IT'S REALITY TV.
>>  THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
A LOT OF US ARE INVESTED WHO
HAVE BEEN WATCHING ALL
38 AND SEASONS.
WE HAVE A LITTLE SOUND OF IT.
>>  SHE HAS THAT LACK OF
CONCERN ABOUT HOW YOU SEE
HER.
I LOVE HER.
ONE OF THE REASONS I LIKE HER
IS THAT SHE IS OLD
ENOUGH TO NOT CARE WHAT YOU
THINK ABOUT HER BUT SHE
DOESN'T HAVE AN EDGE BECAUSE OF
IT.
SHE JUST DOESN'T CARE.
I'M ME AND I WILL BE ME AND IF
YOU LIKE IT I WILL
GET ALONG AND IF YOU DON'T I
WILL TRY TO VOTE YOU
OFF, NO BIG DEAL.
>>  NO BIG DEAL.
>>  THAT'S TRUE.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I HOPE EVERYBODY IN THE WORLD
HAS THAT ATTITUDE.
WHY SHOULD YOU CARE WHAT
SOMEONE ELSE THINKS ABOUT
YOU
IF YOU ARE PROUD OF YOURSELF
AND YOU CARRY YOURSELF
IN A WAY THAT'S KIND TO OTHERS,
WHO CARES WHAT
ANYONE THINKS
I HOPE THAT MY KIDS FEEL THAT
WAY.
I NEVER WANT THEM TO LIVE A
LIFE WORRIED ABOUT WHAT
EVERYBODY ELSE HAS TO SAY ABOUT
THEM.
>>  THE STRESS ISN'T WORTH IT.
IT'S A WASTE OF TIME TO THINK.
YOU ARE MOM TO THREE TEENAGERS.
WHAT DID THE KIDS THINK
>>  THAT'S WHAT MADE THIS SO
EASY.
THEY ARE SO RIDICULOUSLY
SUPPORTIVE AND SO SWEET.
I FEEL BAD ALMOST WHEN I READ
EVERYBODY'S BIO AND
THEY ARE LIKE -- PICTURE MY
FAMILY AND I'M LIKE I
DON'T HAVE DEMENTIA.
I WANT A HOODIE.
I WANT PANTS.
I WANT TO BE COVERED UP.
I DON'T WANT BUG BITES.
>>  YOU JUST WANT A BLANKET.
>>  NO, I DON'T WANT THAT.
I WANT TO BE COVERED UP HEAD TO
TOE AND I DON'T WANT
TO MISS ANYONE BECAUSE I KNOW
THEY ARE OKAY.
WE ARE GOOD.
>>  I WANT TO READ YOUR PET
PEEVE IS E. HUMMING,
INTOLERANCE, SLOBS.
ON AN ISLAND WITH NO TOILET
TISSUE HOW DO YOU DEAL
WITH ALL THAT
>>  IT IS WHAT IT IS.
I DON'T LIKE INTOLERANCE.
IF YOU ARE GOING TO BE RUDE.
IF YOU ARE GOING TO SAY
SOMETHING THAT'S NOT
APPROPRIATE I'M GOING TO SAY
SOMETHING BECAUSE I
DON'T LIKE WHAT YOU JUST SAID.
THAT'S NOT COOL.
IF I DON'T SAY IT TO YOUR FACE
NOW I WILL BE SURE TO
LET YOU KNOW BEFORE WE ARE DONE
AND OVER WITH.
WHAT YOU SAID WAS NOT OKAY.
I DON'T LIKE THAT.
WHY SHOULD ANYONE BE INTOLERANT
NOSE PICKING
DON'T DO IT IN FRONT OF ME.
>>  YOU ARE GOING TO BE FUN TO
WATCH.
>>  CONGRATULATIONS.
>>  SO GOOD TO HAVE YOU HERE.
SURVIVOR PREMIERES TOMORROW AT
8:00 RIGHT HERE ON
WUSA9.
ALL RIGHT.
WE WILL BE BACK WITH MORE AFTER
THIS.
>>  THANK YOU.
>>> UP NEXT A YOUNG NORTHERN ER
TRAVELS TO THE
.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
A CURRENTA YOUNG GIRL TRAVELS
TO THE SOUTH FOR THE FIRST TIME
TO EXPLORE THE CIVIL RIGHTS
TRAIL.
>>  WHAT SHE FOUND REVEALS
TRUTH ABOUT HER FAMILY
HISTORY AND THE NATION'S
PAINFUL PAST IN REGARD TO
RACIAL RELATIONS.
LYNN IS THE WRITER BEHIND THE
ARTICLE AND IS HERE
NOW WITH MORE.
WELCOME TO GREAT DAY.
>>  THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
GREAT TO BE HERE.
>>  IT'S FASCINATING THAT
NATIONAL GEOGRAPHIC
DECIDES TO VENTURE WITH IN OUR
COUNTRY.
WHAT MADE YOU DECIDE TO GO TO
THE SOUTH AND DOCUMENT
YOUR EXPERIENCE
>>  I'M FROM BROOKLYN NEW YORK.
I HAVEN'T SPENT MUCH TIME IN
THE SOUTH.
GOING TO THE DEEP SOUTH FELT
LIKE A TRIP INTO MY
FAMILY'S HISTORY.
I WANTED TO CONNECT TO BLACK
CULTURE WITH FOOD AND
HISTORY AND I WANTED TO
EXPERIENCE IT ON THE GROUND.
ALSO BECAUSE I'M FROM BROOKLYN
I CAN'T DRIVE.
I BROUGHT MY DAD ALONG.
IT BECAME THIS REALLY AMAZING
FATHER, DAUGHTER ROAD
TRIP WHICH MADE IT EVEN MORE
SPECIAL.
>>  YOU WENT ALONG THE UNITED
STATES CIVIL RIGHTS
TRAIL.
WAS THAT A GOOD WAY TO EXPLORE
WHAT -- I THINK
THAT'S FAIRLY NEW.
>>  YEAH.
THE UNITED STATES CIVIL RIGHTS
TRAIL IS GROWING AND
EXPANDING AS THE DAYS GO ON.
IT'S A -- IT'S A NATIONWIDE
TRAIL THAT INCLUDES A
LOT OF DIFFERENT, IMPORTANT
SITES.
THERE'S THE CHURCHES WHERE --
ACTIVISTS WENT AND
ARGUED TO MARCH FROM SELMA TO
MONTGOMERY.
WHERE MARTIN LUTHER KING
MINISTERED OVER THOSE
CHURCHES ARE ON THE TRAIL.
THE WAYS THAT -- PLACE THAT YOU
WOULDN'T EXPECT,
MAYBE A RESTAURANT WHERE PEOPLE
TOOK MEETINGS COULD
BY ON THE TRAIL.
PLACES WHERE HISTORY WAS
ACTIVELY MADE.
YOU CAN EXPERIENCE THAT ALL
THROUGHOUT THE COUNTRY.
I SPECIFICALLY PICKED ALABAMA
BECAUSE IT'S SORT OF
THE HOT BED OF THE CIVIL RIGHTS
MOVEMENT.
YOU KNOW BIRMINGHAM WAS CALLED
BOMBINGHAM BECAUSE OF
ALL OF THE BOMBS SET OFF THERE.
THERE'S A LOT OF PAINFUL
HISTORY IN ALABAMA THAT
SPARKED A LOT OF THE CHANGE IN
THE COUNTRY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS IMPORTANT TO
GO THERE.
>>  YOU LEARNED ABOUT YOUR
FAMILY HISTORY AND NOT
HAVING EVER VENTURED THROUGH
ALABAMA, THINGS WERE
FAMILIAR TO YOU.
IN WHAT WAY
>>  BEING FROM THE NORTH ITS
INTERESTING.
BEING FROM NEW YORK CITY.
I WOULD SAY THAT THE BLACK
EXPERIENCE THERE IS VERY
DIFFERENT.
MY FRIENDS WERE FIRST
GENERATION FROM WEST AFRICA.
I HAD ALL OF THESE INTERACTIONS
WITH A LOT OF
DIFFERENT PARTS OF BLACKNESS.
SPECIFICALLY LIKE BLACK
AMERICAN IDENTITY.
I FELT LIKE THAT WAS RICH AND
TRUE IN THE SOUTH.
THERE WERE THINGS LIKE I WOULD
GO -- MY FAMILY IS
FROM DC.
ON HOLIDAYS I'M EATING LIKE
COLLARED GREENS AND MAC
AND CHEESE AND I KNOW TO PUT A
LITTLE V.INEGAR ON MY
GREENS.
THESE LITTLE CULTURAL THINGS.
>>  YOU MENTIONED THE FRIED
FISH SANDWHICH AND I
RELATED BECAUSE MY FAMILY IS
FROM ALABAMA AND THERE
ARE WAYS WE EAT AND HOW WE
DRESS OUR FOOD THAT IS
CULTURAL AND YOU DON'T
NECESSARILY PINPOINT IT.
>>  I WOULD WATCH HOW WOMEN
WOULD USE THEIR HANDS
AND IT WOULD REMIND ME OF WOMEN
IN MY OWN FAMILY AND
IT FELT BEAUTIFUL TO BE ABLE TO
ANCHOR THESE
EXPERIENCES IN A LARGER
FRAMEWORK.
I FELT SO MUCH RECOGNITION
DURING THAT TRIP.
WE WERE FOLLOWING -- IN SOME
WAYS THE GREEN BOOK.
THE GREEN GUIDE.
STOPPING BY SOME OF THESE
RESTAURANTS THAT ARE NO
LONGER THERE BUT I STARTED TO
THINK ABOUT WHAT IT
WOULD FEEL LIKE TO BE TRAVELING
DURING THE CIVIL
RIGHTS ERA WHERE IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN UNSAFE TO BE ON
THE ROAD AND THAT WAS STRIKING
WHILE THINKING ABOUT
BEING IN THE CAR THAT IF WE DID
THIS DECADES AGO IT
WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN THE SAME.
I WAS VERY AWARE OF WHERE I
FELT SAFE, WHERE I FELT
SEEN, WHERE I FELT -- LIKE I
COULD RECOGNIZE MYSELF
IN OTHER PEOPLE.
IT HAPPENED THROUGHOUT THE
WHOLE EXPERIENCE.
IT WAS REALLIY AFFIRMING.
>>  THANK YOU FOR SHARING THE
STORY WITH US.
>>  I'M SO EXCITED TO SHARE
THIS WITH PEOPLE AT
HOME.
IF YOU WANT TO READ THE FULL
STORY OF HER EYE
OPENING ROAD TRIP ALONG THE
CIVIL RIGHTS TRAIL IT'S
IN THE CURRENT ISSUE OF
NATIONAL GEOGRAPHIC
TRAVELER.
GO PICK IT UP.
>>> HEAR ABOUT THE PLANS FOR A
NEW MEGA HOSPITAL
THAT WILL IMPR
This is not a bed.
It's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed is on sale now
from $899, during the
Ultimate Sleep Number Event.
It senses your movement,
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
It even helps with this.
So you wake up ready to
hit the ground running.
Only at a Sleep Number store.
It's the final days
to save 50% on the
Sleep Number 360 Limited
Edition smart bed.
Plus, 24-month financing
on all smart beds.
Ends Sunday.
Sleep Number.
Proven, quality sleep.
.
>>> A MAJOR NEW HOSPITAL CENTER
THAT'S UNDER
CONSTRUCTION RIGHT NOW WILL
CHANGE THE FACE  OF
MEDICAL CARE.
>>  WE ARE JOINED BY THE SENIOR
VICE PRESIDENT AND
CHIEF MEDICAL DOCTOR.
WELCOME AND CONGRATULATIONS.
THIS IS AN INCREDIBLE,
FACILITY.
>>  THANK YOU.
THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>>  WHAT CAN WE EXPECT
I KNOW IT'S STILL IN
CONSTRUCTION.
YOU ARE IN CHARGE.
WHAT IS YOUR GOAL AND YOUR
VISION FOR THIS FACILITY
>>  NOT ONLY IS THE
CONSTRUCTION HAPPENING BUT WE
ARE ON TIME.
>>  NICE.
>>  WITH THE CONSTRUCTION.
FOR THOSE WHO MAY BE PASSING
THROUGH WE ARE VISIBLE
FROM THE BELTWAY.
PLEASE TAKE A LOOK.
WE ARE ABOUT EIGHT OR NINE
STORIES OUT OF THE GROUND
AND VERY PROUD OF THE PROGRESS
THAT'S BEING MADE.
>>  YOU SEE THE MAP ON THE
SCREEN HERE.
YOU HAVE A COMMUNITY DRIVEN
MISSION WITH THIS NEW
FACILITY.
TELL US ABOUT THAT.
>>  ABSOLUTELY..
WE RECOGNIZE THAT HEALTH CARE
IN ANY COMMUNITY IS
BIGGER THAN JUST THE HOSPITAL.
OUR HEALTH SYSTEM.
THE UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND
HEALTH SYSTEM IS ONE THAT
IS ANCHORED BY A NEW HOSPITAL
WHICH WILL BE IN
LARGO.
WE ALSO HAVE TWO OTHER
FACILITIES WHICH PROVIDE
SERVICES FOR THOSE COMMUNITIES
AND ARE LINKED TO THE
FLAG SHIP HOSPITAL WHICH WILL
BE THE UNIVERSITY OF
MARYLAND, REGION MEDICAL
CENTER.
>>  WHAT THEY LOVE SO MUCH.
WE WERE JUST CHATTING ABOUT
UNIVERSITY OF MEDICAL
SYSTEM.
BEING IN THIS AREA IS HAVING
ACCESS TO THOSE DOCTORS
MEANS YOU HAVE ACCESS TO THE
WHOLE SYSTEM.
THESE DOCTORS TALK TO EACH
OTHER.
THEY ARE ALWAYS MEETING EVERY
WEEK.
YOUR CASE, YOUR SITUATION, YOUR
ISSUE WILL BE SEEN
BY SOME OF THE BEST DOCTORS IN
THE NATION.
>>  YES.
I'M GLAD YOU MENTIONED THAT.
THE ASSOCIATION WITH THE
UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND
MEDICAL SYSTEM WHICH HAPPENED
IN SEPTEMBER OF 2017
BRINGS ACCESS TO A WHOLE RANGE
OF SPECIALISTS AND
FACULTY.
AS A RESULT WE NOW HAVE THREE
GROUPS OF DOCTORS WHO
SUPPORT THE HEALTH SYSTEM, THE
DOCTORS WHO HAVE BEEN
A PART OF THE COMMUNITY AND A
PART OF THE HOSPITAL
CENTER FOR A LONG TIME.
THE NEW DOCTORS WHO ARE PART OF
THE UNIVERSITY EVER
MARYLAND MEDICAL SCHOOL WHO
HAVE BEEN ON THE GROUND
AND RUNNING SEVERAL OF THE KEY
SERVICES FOR SEVERAL
YEARS NOW.
ALSO, WE ARE VERY EXCITED ABOUT
THE NEW DOCTORS WHO
WE ARE ABLE TO NOW RECRUIT
THROUGH THIS VERY
EXCITING PROJECT AND WHO ARE
EXCITED TO COME ON
BOARD  WITH US.
THAT COOPERATION ACROSS
DOCTORS, ACADEMIC AND THOSE
WHO WE WILL HIRE IS CRITICALLY
IMPORTANT.
>>  I WANT TO COMMEND YOU ON
YOUR CONSCIOUS
LEADERSHIP WHEN YOU ARE
THINKING ABOUT THE EXISTING
DOCTORS WHO ARE IN THE COUNTY.
YOU ARE BRINGING IN ALL OF THE
NEW DOCTORS AND YOU
HAVE THIS AMAZING FACILITY.
TELL US ABOUT THE SERVICE THAT
WILL BE OFFERED AND
THE FEATURES, SOME OF THEM YOU
SEE ON THE SCREEN
THAT PEOPLE WILL BE ABLE TO
RECEIVE AND IMPROVE
THEIR HEALTH STATUS RIGHT IN
THE COMMUNITY WHERE
THEY LIVE.
>>  AGAIN, THIS IS GOING BE A
STATE-OF-THE-ART,
600,000 SQUARE FOOT FACILITY
LOCATED IN LARGO.
IT'LL BE A 205 BED FACILITY.
A TRAUMA CENTER.
ALSO, THE COUNTY'S ONLY
NEONATAL INTENSIVE CARE
UNIT.
ALSO A VERY HIGHLY RECOGNIZED
CARDIAC SURGERY
PROGRAM WHICH I THINK YOU HAVE
HEARD ABOUT AS WELL
AS A STROKE PROGRAM.
THE REASON THAT IT'S IMPORTANT
FOR THE FLAG SHIP
FACILITY TO CONTINUE THESE
SERVICES FOR THE COUNTY
AND THE SURROUNDING COMMUNITIES
IS THAT THE DISEASE
BURDEN THAT WE ALL KNOW WELL
HAS BEEN AFFECTING THE
RESIDENTS OF THE COUNTY AND
SURROUNDING COUNTIES.
HAVEN'T BEEN PROPERLY ADDRESSED
ON A POPULATION
BASIS.
NOW WITH A -- A NOT ONLY A NEW
FACILITY WHICH WITH
THESE HIGH END SERVICES BUT
ALSO A NETWORK OF OTHER
PARTS OF OUR HEALTH SYSTEM.
ALSO A NUMBER OF
PRACTICES, COMMUNITY PRACTICES
WHERE OUR RESIDENTS
CAN RECEIVE SERVICES OUTSIDE
THE HOSPITAL AND IT'S
REALLY IMPORTANT THAT ALL OF
THOSE ARE CONNECTED AND
THAT IS WHAT I DO EVERY DAY
ALONG WITH MY COLLEAGUES
AND WE ARE EXCITED ABOUT THE
PROSPECT.
>>  AND THIS IS YOUR
NEIGHBORHOOD.
YOU GET TO WORK THREE MILES
FROM HOME NOW.
THIS IS GREAT.
CONGRATULATIONS ON ALL OF THE
INCREDIBLE STUFF YOU
ARE BRINGING TO THE COUNTY.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THE
FINISHED PROJECT.
THANK YOU.
>>  THANK YOU FOR YOUR SERVICE
TO THE COMMUNITY.
IF YOU WOULD LIKE MORE
INFORMATION ABOUT UPCOMING
UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND, CAPITOL
REGION MEDICAL
CENTER, VISIT UM CAPITOL
REGION.ORG.
>>> YOUR HEALTH MATTERS SO WE
ARE HOLDING FREE
HEALTH SCREENINGS THIS
THURSDAY, FEBRUARY 21th ON
PINE BROOK AVENUE IN LANDOVER.
IT'S CALLED IMPACT, HEALTH
MATTERS.
IT STARTS AT NOON AND GOES
UNTIL 7:00 P.M.
>>  NOON TO SEVEN.
WE ARE PARTNERING WITH YOU AND
CAPITOL REGION HEALTH
TO PROVIDE A WIDE ASSORTMENT OF
SCREENINGS AND DEMO
S AND 20 DIFFERENT SCREENINGS
AND DEMOS  TO BE EXACT.
A FEW OF THEM ARE ON THE
SCREEN.
THERE WILL BE DOCTORS ON HAND
TO ANSWER YOUR
QUESTIONS AND YOU CAN EVEN GIVE
BACK TO THE
COMMUNITY BY DONATING BLOOD.
WHILE THE SCREENINGS ARE FREE,
YOU DO NEED TO
REGISTER FOR SOME OF THEM AS
WELL AS THE BLOOD DRIVE
AHEAD OF TIME.
PLEASE DO THAT.
>>  IT'S EASY.
JUST GO TO WUSA9.COM/HEALTH
MATTERS.
AGAIN, WUSA9.COM/HEALTH
REGISTER FOR SOME OF THE
SCREENINGS BUT REMEMBER,
IT'S ALL FREE.
WE HOPE TO SEE ON THURSDAY.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>> UP NEXT GET READY FOR HEART
HEALTHY RECIPES AND
DISHES FROM OCEAN AIRS
EXECUTIVE CHEF.
.
>>  AND WE ARE GETTING READY
FOR A HIT OF WINTER
WEATHER.
UP TO SIX INCHES OF
.
>>> WE ARE BRACING FOR WINTER
WEATHER.
TOMORROW AROUND THIS TIME WE
WILL GET MODERATE TO
HEAVY SNOW.
HERE IS HOW MUCH WE EXPECT AND
THE TIME IT'LL START.
EVERYWHERE IN THIS WHITE COLOR.
THREE TO SIX INCHES ACROSS DC
METRO.
THAT INCLUDES ANDREWS, COLLEGE
PARK, SILVER SPRINGS,
FAIRFAX,   FALLS CHURCH.
HIGHER AMOUNTS OF SLEET AND
SNOW COMBINES, SIX TO
EIGHT INCHES ALONG WESTMINISTER
AND THESE AREAS WILL
START EARLIER AND BE A BIT
HEAVIER AT TIMES.
THE LOWER AMOUNTS ONE TO THREE
INCHES.
THOSE AREAS WE ARE THINKING
THAT IS -- WE WILL SEE A
TRANSITION TO RAIN AND FREEZING
RAIN AND SLEET A
LITTLE EARLIER IN THOSE SPOTS.
START TIME, 4:00 A.M.
TO 5:00 A.M.
ALONG WINCHESTER
AND MARTINSBURG. THEN ROUGHLY
SIX TO SEVEN AS YOU HEAD ALONG
THE
EASTERN SHORE.
HERE ARE THE MAIN THREATS.
WE WILL HAVE THAT CHANCE TO GET
SOME HEAVY SNOW
AROUND HERE, SOME SHOWERS AND A
MIX OF WINTER
WEATHER WHICH ALSO INCLUDES
SLEET AND FREEZING RAIN
THAT WILL LEAD TO ICING IN A
FEW SPOTS.
SO, HOUR BY HOUR THIS IS WHAT
IT LOOKS LIKE
TOMORROW.
5:00 A.M.
WINCHESTER, LEESBURG GETTING
SNOW.
AT 6:30 A.M.
THE SNOW ACROSS FREDRICKBU RG.
BY THE 7:00 A.M.
HOUR MOST AREAS ARE GETTING
LIGHT
TO MODERATE SNOW.
WE WILL DEAL WITH THAT HEAVIER
SNOW AROUND THE AREA.
YOU HAVE THE TEMPERATURES CLOSE
TO THE FREEZING MARK
IT.
GIVES YOU THAT WET, HEAVIER
TYPE OF SNOW.
WE WILL START TO SEE A
TRANSITION FROM A MIX OVER TO
RAIN.
YOU WILL SEE THAT FIRST AROUND
FREDRICKSBURG.
WE HAVE A WINTER MIX GOING ON,
A WINTER MESS WITH
THE FREEZING RAIN AND SLEET AND
THEN BY 430 ACTION
IN THE AFTERNOON TEMPERATURES
COME ABOVE FREEZING
AND WE WILL SEE THAT TRANSITION
OVER TO RAIN.
UNLESS YOU ARE IN THE NORTHERN
SUBURBS, ONLY ADDING
TO THE POTENTIAL FOR ICE
ACCUMULATION.
TWO TENTHS OF AN INCH POSSIBLE
ALLOWANCE LEESBURG.
OUR NORTHERN SUBURBS COULD SEE
A LITTLE MORE ICE
FORMING AND THAT'S A PROBLEM.
YOU HAVE SEVERAL INCHES OF SNOW
AND WILL PUT ICE ON
TOP OF IT.
IT'S LIKE THE ONE, TWO PUNCH OF
WINTER WEATHER THAT
WE WILL BE SEEING.
THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE
TAKING THE STORM
SERIOUSLY.
ISSUING A WINTER STORM WARNING.
WE WILL START AT 1:00 WEDNESDAY
MORNING AND LAST
UNTIL 7:00 WEDNESDAY EVENING.
THE SEVEN DAY FORECAST YOU WILL
NOTICE TEMPERATURES
IN THE 40'S.
SNOW AND A MIX CHANGING OVER TO
RAIN.
ONCE WE GET PAST WEDNESDAY
MOTHER NATURE MAKING UP
TO US.
RAIN CHANCES BUT TEMPERATURES
WILL HEAD TO THE 50'S
AND 60'S BY SUNDAY.
>>> TODAY IN THE GREAT DAY
KITCHEN WE ARE FOCUSING
ON HEART HEALTHY SEAFOOD
SPECIALITIES WITH THE
EXECUTIVE CHEF OF OCEAN AIR.
WELCOME BACK.
>>  THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>>  LOVE ALL THE BEAUTY HERE.
I THINK IT'S GOOD TO REMIND
PEOPLE THAT THE FISH AND
SEAFOOD IS GOOD FOR YOUR HEART.
>>  THEY ARE VISIBLE IN ALL OF
THESE FOODS I HAVE
HERE.
OMEGA3 IN THAT.
WE HAVE ALL KINDS OF DIFFERENT
SEAFOOD.
MARYLAND ROCK FISH.
A NICE LOCAL FAVORITE AS WELL.
>>  WHEN -- LET ME ASK YOU
ABOUT THE OYSTERS.
NOT TO PUT YOU ON THE SPOT.
RAW -- WHEN YOU COOK THEM OR --
DO -- WHAT IS IT
DO YOU LOOSE ANY OF THE
NUTRIENTS
>>  THEY ARE STILL RIGHT IN
THERE.
ANYTHING YOU ADD IS JUST A
BONUS FOR THE FLAVOR.
>>  IF YOU DON'T LIKE THE RAW
ONES YOU CAN TRY IT IS
OTHER WAY.
SALMON.
WE KNOW THAT'S GOOD FOR YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU MAKING FOR US
>>  THIS PREPARATION MEANS IN
PAPER.
THIS IS A GREAT PREPARATION TO
GO AT HOME.
LITTLE CLEAN UP AND IT'S EASY
TO DO.
I PUT VEGETABLES DOWN HERE.
>>  THOSE ARE RAW.
>>  RAW.
ALL THE STUFF IS RAW GOING INTO
THE PAPER AND THEN
INTO THE OVEN.
YOU PUT A LITTLE BIT OF
SEASONING ON TOP OF THAT AND
THEN AROMATICS.
YOU CAN SEASON IT HOW YOU WANT.
YOU CAN PUT CITRUS, GARLIC,
LEMON JUICE, CHERRY
TOMATOES.
YOU CAN JUST FOLD THE PAPER
AROUND THE SALMON.
IT CREATES A NICE STEAM POCKET.
WHEN YOU DO THAT YOU JUST PULL
IT AROUND THERE AND
YOU FOLD IT UP.
YOU WANT TO CREATE AS TIGHT A
SEAL AS POSSIBLE TO
PUT THE SEAM IN THERE.
WHAT YOU WILL HAVE IS THIS
CIRCLE OF PARCHMENT
PAPER.
YOU DON'T WANT ANYTHING WITH
WAX BECAUSE YOU ARE
STEAMING.
THEN YOU WILL JUST FINISH
FOLDING IT LIKE THAT.
THEN PUT IT INTO A 425-DEGREE
OVEN FOR ABOUT 20
MINUTES AND YOU WILL GET
SOMETHING THAT COMES OUT
SIMILAR TO THIS.
THIS IS PREPARED.
JUST SEE A LITTLE.
>>  LIKE A SALMON BURRITO.
ALL GOOD FOR YOU.
>>  FRESH THYME AND THE LEMON
WEDGES IN THERE FLAVOR
IT UP VERY NICELY.
>>  LOOK AT THE STEAM COMING
OUT.
>>  THIS IS ALWAYS ONE YOU CAN
HAVE WITH PARTIES AND
STUFF.
YOU CAN PREPARE IT AHEAD OF
TIME.
GREAT TO HAVE WITH FAMILY AND
STUFF.
ANOTHER WAY I LIKE TO FLAVOR
THINGS IS WITH VINEGAR
AND STUFF.
IT'S A LOW FAT WAY OF  ADDING
FLAVOR TO A FISH.
THERE'S ALL KINDS OF FISH.
IF YOU LIKE SARDIN ES THIS IS
JUST A SIMPLE
VINEGRETTE.
LITTLE BIT OF FRESH THYME.
>>  THAT LOOKS AMAZING.
YOU ARE AT THE DC LOCATION
WHICH IS WHERE
>>  1205F STREET ACROSS FROM
THE METRO STATION.
>>  HOW MUCH FUN.
IT HAS TO BE FUN FOR YOU TO
FIND ALL OF THESE
DIFFERENT SEAFOODS THAT COME
IN.
>>  WE ARE ABLE TO ACCESS
THINGS ALL OVER THE WORLD.
ALASKA, NEW ZEALAND.
ALL KIND OF OYSTERS AND FRESH
FISH.
WE FLY IT IN DAILY.
>>  THANK YOU FOR SHARING THIS
EASY AT HOME RECIPE.
IF YOU DON'T FEEL LIKE MAKING
ANYTHING, COME SEE
CHEF HERE AT OCEAN AIR AND GET
THIS HEART HEALTHY
SEAFOOD IN FOR YOU.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
GREAT TO SEE YOU.
YOUR HEALTH MATTERS TO US.
THAT'S WHY WE BRING THIS
INFORMATION TO YOU.
THAT'S WHY WE ARE HOLDING FREE
HEALTH SCREENINGS
THIS THURSDAY, FEBRUARY 21th ON
PINE BROOK AVENUE
IN LA NDOVER.
IT'S CALLED IMPACT HEALTH
MATTERS.
STARTS AT NOON AND GOES UNTIL
7:00 P.M.
WE ARE
PARTNERING THE CAPITOL REGION
HEALTH AND THE HEALTH
DEPARTMENT TO PROVIDE A WIDE
ASSORTMENT OF
SCREENINGS AND DEMOS.
YOU CAN DO IT BY GOING TO THE
WEBSITE AND REGISTER.
ALL THE SCREENINGS ARE FREE.
REMEMBER THIS THURSDAY FROM
NOON TO SEVEN, NO
EXCUSES.
WE WILL SEE YOU THERE.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>> COMING UP LEARN HOW TO SAVE
ON THE BEST
MANUFACTURER NAMES, STYLES AND
Cancer won't wait for
appointments to open up,
test results to come back,
or treatment plans to start.
At Cancer Treatment Centers of
America,
we make time for cancer
patients.
Time to answer questions,
relieve worries,
and turn indecision into good
decisions.
Because cancer won't wait,
and we don't think you should
either.
Call or go online anytime
to set up an appointment with
our team of cancer experts.
Cancer Treatment Centers of
America.
Appointments available now.
.
>>> THERE ARE SO MANY CHOICES
WHEN IT COMES TO
HAVING YOUR FLOORING REPLACED.
LAURA IS FROM 50 FLOOR IS HERE
TO TALK ABOUT THE
BENEFITS OF GETTING NEW
FLOORING INSTALLED.
WELCOME BACK TO GREAT DAY.
>>  THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>>  WE HAVE OPTIONS BETWEEN THE
INTERNET AND LOOKING
UP PEOPLE, JUST WORD OF MOUTH.
WHY SHOULD SOMEONE PICK 50
FLOOR
>>  WE OFFER THIS TOP NAME-
BRAND AND WHAT THAT MEANS
IS WHEN WE BRING THE SHOWROOM
TO YOU.
WHEN YOU GET TO SEE ALL THE
SAMPLES WE HAVE WE
DISPLAY THE MANUFACTURER NAME,
THE STYLES AND
COLORS.
SOME OF OUR COMPETITION USE
PRIVATE LABELS.
THAT MAKES IT HARD TO COMPARE
APPLES TO APPLES.
WE WANT YOU TO KNOW WE CARRY
MOHAWK, DREAM WEAVER,
SOME OF THE TOP BRANDS, THE
BEST COLORS, OF COURSE
AND THE TOP WARRANTIES THAT ARE
AVAILABLE AS WELL.
THAT'S ANOTHER BENEFIT OF 50
FLOOR.
IF YOU HAVE AN ISSUE WE WILL
CONTACT THE
MANUFACTURER.
WE WANT TO TAKE CAR OF OUR
CUSTOMERS.
WITH OTHER COMPETITION LIKE
EMPIRE YOU ARE LEFT
HAVING TO MAKE THAT CALL
YOURSELF AND DEAL WITH
THAT.
WE REALLY WANT TO MAKE THE
PROCESS SMOOTH.
>>  INTERESTING.
TELL ME ABOUT THE DEALS THAT
YOU HAVE FOR GREAT DAY
VIEWERSO ERS ON TOP OF THAT.
>>  WE ARE OFFERING 60% OFF ALL
FLOORING MATERIAL.
NO MATTER WHAT MANUFACTURER YOU
PICK, WHAT TYPE OF
FLOORING, THAT COULD BE CARPET,
HARD WOOD, VINYL,
TILE, YOU ARE GOING TO SAVE 60%
OFF ANY MATERIAL
THAT YOU PICK.
>>  AND YOU VISIT PEOPLE WHERE
THEY ARE AT.
YOU GO TO THEIR HOMES.
>>  THAT'S RIGHT.
OUR FREE AT HOME CONSULTATION
IS A GREAT WAY TO SEE
EVERYTHING.
WE BRING THE SHOWROOM TO YOU.
VIEWERS CAN CALL OR VISIT THE
WEBSITE 50 FLOOR.COM
TO GET THAT SCHEDULED TODAY.
OUR DESIGN EXPERT WILL COME AND
BRING HUNDREDS OF
SAMPLES, THAT WAY YOU CAN
ACTUALLY SEE HOW THEY LOOK
IN YOUR OWN SPACE WHERE YOU ARE
PLANNING TO GET IT
INSTALLED.
YOU CAN SEE IT WITH YOUR OWN
LIGHTING.
YOU AREN'T WONDERING HOW IT
LOOKS IN A SHOWROOM.
YOU CAN SEE IT UP CLOSE IN YOUR
OWN SPACE.
>>  ONCE A HOMEOWNER DECIDES,
OKAY, I WILL GET THIS
NEW FLOORING.
WHAT HAPPENS ON INSTALLATION
DAY
>>  YOU KNOW INSTALLATION DAY
IS WHERE WE SHINE.
WE GET SOME GREAT FEEDBACK AND
CUSTOMERS JUST LOVE
OUR TOP NOTCH SERVICE.
WHEN WE SHOW UP OUR CREW WILL
MOVE AND LIFT YOUR
HEAVY FURNITURE AND APPLIANCES
FOR YOU SO YOU DON'T
HAVE TO DO THE HEAVY LIFTING.
WE TAKE CARE OF THAT.
THEN OUR CREW WILL TAKE THAT
EXTRA TIME TO REMOVE
YOUR FLOORING AND CHECK THE
SUBFLOOR TO MAKE SURE
EVERYTHING IS CLEARED OFF, IN
GOOD CONDITION FOR US
TO THEN INSTALL THAT BEAUTIFUL
BRAND NEW FLOORING
THAT YOU HAVE SELECTED.
>>  I LOVE SEEING THOSE GUYS
LIFT THE HEAVY
FURNITURE.
I'M LIKE YES.
IT'S SO HARD WHEN YOU ARE DOING
A HOME IMPROVEMENT
PROJECT AND YOU HAVE TO DO THE
HEAVY LIFTING.
I LIKE THE SOUND OF SOMEONE
ELSE DOING IT,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU ARE
SPENDING YOUR HARD EARNED
MONEY.
YOU ALSO HAVE 0% FINANCING.
>>  ON TOP OF OUR 60% DEAL THAT
0% FINANCING IS A
GREAT WAY TO FINANCE THE BILL
INTEREST FREE AS LONG
AS THE BILL IS PAID OFF WITH IN
THE TERMS OF THE
AGREEMENT.
ONE MORE BONUS.
YOU GET ANOTHER $100 OFF IF YOU
MENTION PROMO CODE
GREAT DAY WASHINGTON.
>>  THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
>>  THANK YOU.
>>  REMEMBER FOR THE MONTH OF
FEBRUARY YOU CAN GET
60% OFF ON FLOORING MATERIALS
AND WE HAVE THAT
ADDITIONAL TREAT FOR YOU.
JUST MENTION GREAT DAY
WASHINGTON.
JUST ONE TIME OR YOU CAN
MENTION IT THREE TIMES.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO TO GET
STARTED IS CALL BEFORE THE
END OF THE SHOW, SCHEDULE A
FREE HOME CONSULTATION
AND GET $100 OFF.
CALL WITH IN THE HOUR AND GET
STARTED ON YOUR NEW
FLOOR TODAY.
>>> IF YOU ARE FINDING IT HARD
TO MANAGE DIABETES
IT'S TIME FOR A NEW APPROACH.
FIND OUT HOW TO GET BACK TO THE
BEST HEALTH EVER
Z35K8Z Z16FZ
Y35K8Y Y16FY
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
.
>>> CURRENTLY IT'S ESTIMATED
THAT HALF THE
POPULATION OF THE UNITED STATES
HAS DIABETES OR HAS
PREDIABETES.
THE STATS AREN'T SLOWING DOWN
EVEN WITH ALMOST
DIFFERENT 50 DIABETES
MEDICATIONS ON THE MARKET.
ACCORDING TO AARP, 65-YEAR-
OLD'S IN THE COUNTRY ARE
TAKING AN AVERAGE OF FIVE
DIFFERENT MEDICATIONS EACH
DAY WITH THE AVERAGE FOR ALL
TYPE 2 BEING NINE PER
DAY.
HERE WITH US TODAY ARE DOCTORS
TOM AND STEPHANIE
CHENEY OF LIVING HEALTH
INTEGRATED MEDICATION TO
SHARE THE DIFFERENT APPROACHES
TO DIABETES.
ONE THAT IS HELPING PATIENTS
REVERSE THEIR
CONDITION.
WELCOME BACK TO THE SHOW.
>>  THANK YOU.
>>  I WANT TO START WITH YOU.
HOW CAN PEOPLE HAVE SO MANY
MEDICATIONS AVAILABLE ON
THE MARKET THAT TREAT DIABETES
AND THEN THE RATES
ARE STILL GROWING
>>  THAT'S A GREAT QUESTION.
MOST PATIENTS COME TO US AND
THEY ARE UNDER
CONVENTIONAL TREATMENT.
THEY ARE GOING TO SEE THEIR
DOCTOR AND UNFORTUNATELY
MOST CONVENTIONAL TREATMENT IS
GEARED TOWARD THE
MANAGEMENT OF THE SYMPTOMS AND
TRYING TO SLOW DOWN
THE PROGRESSION OF THE DISEASE.
YOU KNOW TREAT THE SYMPTOMS AND
THE -- THE SIDE
EFFECTS AND COMPLICATIONS THAT
COME ALONG WITH IT
LIKE HEART ATTACKS, STROKE,
THINGS THAT HAVE REALLY
ONSET ALZHEIMER'S.
THERE'S A LOT OF CONDITIONS
THAT COME ALONG WITH
PROGRESSION OF THIS DISEASE.
SO, WHAT WE WANT TO DO IS NOT
-- BE REACTIVE ABOUT
TREATING THIS DISEASE.
WE WANT TO BE PROACTIVE.
OUR MODEL IS GEARED TOWARD
ACTUALLY TREATING THE
ROOT CAUSES OF THE DISEASE.
SO WE TAKE A FUNCTIONAL
MEDICINE MODEL AND WHAT WE
SEE IS THERE'S MANY DIFFERENT
CAUSES OF THIS
DISEASE.
WE GO AFTER THE CAUSES AND THEN
WE ARE ABLE TO SEE
THAT OVERTIME THE DISEASE CAN
BE REVERSED.
>>  OKAY.
YOU SAY CAUSES WHICH DEBUNKS
THE IDEA THAT DIABETES
IS JUST A POOR FUNCTIONING
PANCREAS.
THAT'S NOT TRUE
>>  IT'S A SIMPLE VIEW OF WHAT
TYPE 2 DIABETES IS.
TYPE 2 DIABETES FROM OUR
PERSPECTIVE AND TESTING IS
RARELY EVEN A PANCREAS.
IT'S THE STRESS BUT IT'S
STRESSED BECAUSE IT'S
DEALING WITH A VERY LARGE OVER
LOAD OF SUGAR AND A
VERY CHALLENGING AMOUNT OF
INSULIN RESISTANCE.
IT'S NOT THAT IT'S NOT WORKING,
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE FOR
IT TO OVERCOME ALL OF THAT
SUGAR.
FOR US IT'S A MATTER OF DOING
TESTING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT ARE ALL THE DIFFERENT
REASONS WHY THE SUGAR IS
COMPLETELY OUT OF CONTROL.
IT'S MORE THAN YOU ATE A BOWL
OF JELLY BEANS AND
YOUR SUGAR WENT UP.
PATIENTS HAVE FIGURED OUT IF
THEY EAT SUGAR THEIR
SUGAR GOES HIGH.
WE SEE A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT
HAVE TRIED TO CHANGE
THEIR DIET, THEY STARTED
EXERCISING, TRYING TO GET
THE SUGAR DOWN AND IT'S NOT
WORKING.
WE DO TESTING, BLOOD, URINE AND
TRY TO FIGURE OUT IS
IT A -- UNDER LYING INFECTION,
OTHER ISSUES LIKE
FOOD ALLERGIES OR VITAMIN
PROBLEMS, GLAND
DISFUNCTION AND THEN WE CAN
CREATE A CUSTOM PROGRAM
THAT WILL ACTUALLY HELP THAT
PERSON GET HEALTHY AND
FUNCTIONING AND THEN THE
PANCREAS IS HAPPY AGAIN.
IT HAS A NORMAL AMOUNT OF
SUGAR.
>>  ISN'T THAT WHAT WE ALL WANT
THERE'S A TEST CALLED HBA1C.
IT SOUNDS LIKE THIS IS MUCH
MORE IN DEPTH THAN JUST
GETTING TESTED EVERY NOW AND
AGAIN FOR THAT AND IT
LEADS TO DIABETES ACTUALLY
BEING REVERSED.
>>  RIGHT.
THAT MARKER.
THE HBA1C IS THE AMOUNT OF RED
BLOOD CELLS DAMAGED
BY BLOOD SUGAR.
IT'S A MARKER THEY LOOK TO
DETERMINE HOW BAD IS YOUR
DIABETES.
HOW POORLY IS IT BEING MANAGED.
DO YOU NEED ANOTHER MEDICATION
ALL IT IS A MARKER FOR THE
DAMAGE CAUSED BY SUGAR.
IT'S NOT TELLING YOU WHERE IS
THAT SUGAR COMING
FROM, WHAT'S THE DAMAGE CAUSED
BY
NORMAL IS 5.7% OR BELOW.
WHEN WE ARE WORKING WITH
SOMEONE WHO COMES IN AND
THEY HAVE A 9.2% LIKE THERESA
WE TALKED TO HAD A
9.2% ON THREE DIFFERENT
MEDICATIONS.
WE WANTED TO GET HER DOWN ON NO
WE GOT HER DOWN LESS THAN TWO
MONTHS TO LESS THAN
6.0%.
A REVERSAL IS GETTING IT DOWN
WHILE THE PATIENT IS
BEING ABLE TO GET TAKEN OFF
MEDICATION.
>>  THIS SOUNDS AMAZING.
YOU HAVE A PROGRAM WHERE PEOPLE
CAN TAKE PART AND BE
LIKE SOME OF YOUR SUCCESS
STORIES.
TELL ME MORE ABOUT THE PROGRAM.
>>  FOR VIEWERS OUT THERE THAT
WANT TO STOP TREATING
SYMPTOMS AND TREAT THE CAUSES
OF THE DISEASE, THAT'S
WHAT WE DO IN THE PROGRAM.
IT'S A FUNCTIONAL MEDICINE
APPROACH.
THEN THEY CAN COME TO THE
SEMINAR.
WE HAVE A DIABETES SOLUTION
THAT'S THE FIRST STEP.
WE TALK ABOUT MYTH THAT
SURROUND TYPE 2 DIABETES.
WE TALK ABOUT HOW WE REVERSE
IT.
THAT'S A FIRST STEP.
COME TO THE SEMINAR.
YOU CAN GO TO OUR WEBSITE
DIABETES REVERSAL
SEMINAR.COM.
YOU CAN CALL (888)514-4771 AND
REGISTER FOR THE
SEMINAR.
WE ARE GIVING A FREE BOOK.
NOT ONLY IS IT A FREE SEMINAR
BUT THE BOOK DEFEAT
DIABETES WE ARE GIVING A COPY
OF THIS TO EACH
PERSON.
>>  THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR THE
GREAT INFORMATION.
I LOVE WHEN YOU SAID OPTIMAL
HEALTH.
THE SOLUTION TO YOUR SUFFERING
IS ONLY A PHONE CALL
AWAY.
IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO SEE IF YOU
QUALIFY PLEASE CALL
OR VISIT DIABETES REVERSAL
SEMINAR.COM.
IF YOU QUALIFY YOU WILL RECEIVE
AN INVITE TO ONE OF
THE NEXT TYPE 2 DIABETES
SOLUTION SEMINARS AND A
FREE BOOK.
DEFEAT DIABETES.
THE NEXT SEMINAR IS 6:00 P.M.
TOMORROW AT LIVING
HEALTH INTEGRATED MEDICINE.
THE FOLLOWING ONE IS SATURDAY
FEBRUARY 23rd AT
10:00 A.M.
AT THE ANNAPOLIS CROWN PLAZA.
DON'T DELAY.
MAKE THAT CALL RIGHT NOW.
(888)514-4771
.
>>> THE MAN IN THE PHOTOGRAPH
FROM 73 YEARS AGO HAS
DIED.
THE PICTURE WAS TAKEN ON AUGUST
14th 1945.
THE JAPANESE HAD JUST
SURRENDERED WHEN THE NAVY
SOLDER GRABBED A SOLDIER AND
KISSED HER.
>>  WE ALL KNOW THIS
PHOTOGRAPH.
GEORGE WAS ON A DATE.
THAT'S HIS DATE RIGHT THERE IN
THE BACK OF THE
PHOTOGRAPH.
HE WAS ON A DATE WITH A WOMAN
NAMED RITA.
HE SHE IS THERE BUT TURNS OUT
SHE WASN'T UPSET.
SHE AND GEORGE WERE MARRIED FOR
MORE THAN 70 YEARS.
WOW.
>>  THANK YOU ALL FOR