to each dish.
That's what my food is about--
flavor, love.
Whew!
Do-or-die time.
I'm ready.
I've been ready.
I need everybody
to kind of start
setting up
their stations, okay?
ARIEL: You guys should be doing
last-minute things right now.
MOTTO: How are we looking
on apps over there, Kanae?
I still got to push out
all these dumplings,
'cause if I don't get them
done now, it's gonna be hell.
MIA: Communicate, okay?
ALL: Yes.
Come on, guys,
let's do a little group huddle.
Please,
always communication,
appetizers, appetizers,
communicate.
I'm gonna talk you guys
through this.
I'm never gonna leave
you alone, all right?
I'm gonna make sure
you guys are okay
the whole step of the way.
I want you supporting him.
When I call the meats,
pull the meats,
and then just help him
whenever possible.
On three, "A-Team."
One, two, three...
ALL: A-Team!
-Let's go. Let's do this.
GORDON: Mia, one final thing.
Ariel, let's go.
Every night when we are ready,
what's the one thing
I do to Marino?
ARIEL: Oh, tell him
to open Hell's Kitchen.
-So can you do it together?
-Together? Yes.
-On the count of three...
-Off you go.
BOTH: One, two, three...
Marino,
open Hell's Kitchen!
Subito.
♪ ♪
NARRATOR: Hell's Kitchen
is the place to be
for this
much-anticipated showdown
between veteran Ariel
and rookie Mia.
Of course the finalists'
families are in attendance...
-To our baby.
-She is our baby.
NARRATOR:
Along with other VIPs.
In Ariel's kitchen, former
O.J. Simpson prosecutor
Marcia Clark will be dining.
Please let me introduce you
to our finalist, Ariel.
Hi. Welcome.
Pleasure to have you
-this evening.
-Thank you.
NARRATOR: While Mia's kitchen
will host actor
and comedian J.B. Smoove.
Wow, bro, this is the joint.
Look at this, man.
Okay, guys, listen up.
Two risotto, one shrimp scampi,
one ceviche.
ALL: Heard.
-Thank you.
MIA: This is it.
It's crunch time.
I have to prove
that I have it in me
to lead an entire kitchen,
and I feel like I'm gonna
surprise Chef Ramsay
with my performance tonight.
How long--two risotto,
shrimp, ceviche?
-Six minutes.
-Heard that.
-Risotto working.
JOSE: Putting Trev on apps,
you know, I would have
went a different route.
That was Mia's decision,
but, you know,
you don't want to start off
slow 'cause then it could
just slow down
the whole service after that.
-Risotto, 30 seconds.
-Okay.
-30 seconds.
-Are you tasting it?
Yes, I'm tasting everything.
More salt.
-More salt. Heard, Chef.
-Mm-hmm.
Season every stage,
every stage.
TREV: Yes, Chef.
-Mia on it, man.
Trev,
I don't need this, dude.
Come on, like,
this is rookie [bleep].
This needs to be perfect.
Walking risotto.
Good job.
Keep it coming, okay?
-Got it.
-Good girl.
Go.
Trev, taste it.
Tasting everything, Chef.
All right, listen up,
Red Team.
-You guys ready for this?
ALL: Yes, Chef.
All right,
we have a four-top,
away--two scallops,
two dumplings.
ALL: Heard, Chef.
ARIEL: My team is amped up.
They are in this,
and I feel like we're gonna
just knock this
out of the park tonight.
KANAE: Scotley, five minutes
all day, okay?
Five minutes, heard.
KANAE: We only have
one shot at tonight,
and we are determined
to have everything
come out perfect for Ariel.
[bleep], Motto, it burnt.
Huh?
-They burnt.
-[bleep].
This is not going
according to plan.
Kanae, get it together.
You got this, baby.
ARIEL: Are we walking two
dumplings with two scallops?
MOTTO: Yes, Chef.
-Yes, right after.
SCOTLEY:
Walking scallops.
ARIEL: Dumplings, let's go.
KANAE: I need 30 seconds, Chef,
and it will be at the window.
Ariel, I've got scallops dying.
We've got to go.
We can't just leave food
hanging like that.
This is your standards.
All right,
I need those two dumplings.
-Let's go, guys.
KANAE: Yes, Chef.
♪ ♪
I need service, please.
Thank God.
I didn't make all these
damn dumplings for nothing.
Rock that [bleep].
NARRATOR: With Kanae's
quick recovery on dumplings...
Thank you, and ceviche
right behind it, please.
NARRATOR: Appetizers
are now making their way
out of both kitchens.
Table 23--this is my family,
VIP, please.
Thank you so much.
-Like mami.
BOTH: Bon appétit.
NARRATOR: And receiving
high praise from the diners.
BOTH: Mmm.
That's phenomenal.
Wow.
-It's pretty damn good.
This risotto is definitely
off the hook.
Fire two sea bass,
two pork.
Two sea bass,
two pork, how long, Roe?
ROE: Two pork,
seven minutes, please.
HEATHER: Seven minutes
to the window, Chef.
MIA: Thank you.
I'm one for one being
on winning brigades,
so I think this
bodes well for Mia.
Two pork in my hand.
Let's go to the promised land.
Pork, hot plate, Chef.
-How long--two sea bass?
-30 seconds.
Come on.
Roe!
Glazing right now, girl.
I'm glazing right now.
I need you up here right now.
She needs you to look
at that pork, Roe.
♪ ♪
The pork is raw, okay?
I need you to flash them.
Heard? How long?
-Two minutes.
HEATHER: Here come
the pork medallions back.
Roe, honey, they're thick.
You need to mark them
and get them in the oven
and let them finish.
If not, you're gonna sell
medium-rare pork again,
and I highly doubt
anybody wants that.
ROE: Heather, come here.
-Yeah, coming.
ROE: Can you check that?
If it's not good,
throw it back in.
GORDON: Why isn't he going?
What are we waiting on?
-We're waiting on pork.
-Oh, [bleep].
-How long, pork?
-Checking it now, Chef.
I don't want
to give you anything raw.
GORDON: Oh, man.
This ain't good.
What the [bleep] is going on?
-How long, pork?
J.B.: Uh-oh.
Roe?
Look around.
With artificial intelligence,
we are not crawling
or walking.
We are flying.
Microsoft AI helps an architect
bring history back to life.
This is now.
AI helps farmers grow more
food with less resources.
An engineer explores how
AI can help the Deaf
see sound.
Innovation creates tomorrow,
and tomorrow is here today.
♪ ♪
♪ Step it up. ♪
♪ Always take the risk. ♪
Don't just watch it...
Put your phone down and do it.
♪ Drip splash like the ice
on the wrist. ♪
♪ Brrt brrt brrt brrt ♪
♪ that's a call I can't miss. ♪
Let's do.
From the first loving touch
Pampers diapers are the #1
Choice of Hospitals,
and have been for over 40 years
Pampers Swaddlers
The #1 Choice of Hospitals,
Nurses & Parents
Not much here,
except the usual.
What if we spice
things up a bit?
Alexa...
"Fire"
by The Ohio Players
♪Fire (uh) (uh)♪
What if we turn it up a notch?
♪Fire (It's all about) (Uh, uh)♪
What if we go off the map?
♪Fire (Woo, woo, woo)♪
♪Fire♪
The all-new RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
[ music playing ]
♪ Here Comes the Sun ♪
You, all of you.
How you live. What you love.
[ laughter ]
That's what inspired us
to create America's
most advanced Internet.
Internet that
puts you in charge.
[ chattering ]
That protects what's important.
That handles everything
[ group cheering ]
and reaches everywhere.
This is beyond WiFi.
This is xFi.
Simple. Easy. Awesome.
Xfinity.
The future of awesome.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
(dramatic music)
NARRATOR: It's 45 minutes into
the final dinner service...
Why isn't he going?
What are we waiting on?
MIA: We're waiting on pork.
-Oh, [bleep]
NARRATOR:
And rookie finalist Mia
has been left waiting on Roe
to deliver
properly cooked pork.
How long, pork?
ROE: One minute
on those refires, Mia.
MIA:
I won the challenge,
and Roe was my first pick
last night.
I thought
she was the strongest,
and this is
a little nerve-racking.
Super hot, super hot.
♪ ♪
-It's done.
-Go, go, go.
Amazing process to watch.
-Scary.
-Very scary.
Guys, listen up,
first entrées--
we're gonna go on
two rib cap, two wagyu.
-How long?
-I need eight minutes, Chef.
Eight minutes, two rib cap,
two wagyu heard.
I've never worked
with Scotley before,
so I'm gonna keep an eye
on him tonight,
and the menu's
a little lighter tonight,
so hopefully Scotley
can keep up.
-Oh, my God. Scotley.
-Right now, Chef.
-Scotley, watch your grill.
SCOTLEY: Heard.
We're charring on
our steaks over here.
SCOTLEY: Heard.
ARIEL: We want perfect
food tonight, okay?
It's not a race.
It always get annoying when,
you know,
you have a backseat driver.
Somebody over your shoulder
telling you how to cook.
Man, I got this.
I been doing this.
We got to watch the grill
because we're getting
too much char.
I would like to start
a couple new ones.
SCOTLEY: Yes, Chef.
ARIEL: Come on, man.
I'm not concerned
about rushing these out.
I want to make sure
we get them to the guests
the way they're intended
to be enjoyed.
All right, I need to see
those rib cap. Bring them up.
SCOTLEY: Bringing it
right now, Chef.
♪ ♪
That's perfectly cooked.
-Not more than this.
-Heard, Chef.
Trust me.
I'm here to help you.
ARIEL:
I need service, please.
Our chef seems
very self-assured.
-Yeah.
-All right, guys, next ticket.
You said three minutes.
You should be 30 seconds out.
Let's go.
Okay, so away now,
two chicken, two churrasco.
ALL: Heard.
HEATHER: Two chicken,
two beef, heard, Chef.
JOSE: Two chicken,
two churrasco.
MIA: Guys, I need five minutes
on that next check,
the two skirt
and the two chicken.
MIA: I'm a little nervous
about Heather.
She just lost to me,
so it may be a little difficult
to motivate her.
Nice sear, nice glaze,
medium-rare.
I just hope
that she can support me.
How long--two chicken,
two churrasco?
Give me three minutes on the
two beef and two chicken, yeah?
I'm all about carrying Mia
to victory,
whether we're BFFs or not.
Chicken and beef are up.
Let me know
when you're ready to walk.
You ready to go, Jose?
Let me go first,
yeah, two chicken.
I'm coming up.
Proteins walking.
Behind, Chef, hot.
Are they rested?
Yes, Chef.
Hopefully I lead Mia
into victory
'cause I know what it's like
to have my hand on that door
and it not open.
It hurts.
♪ ♪
-Heather, beautiful cook...
-Yes?
-On the protein.
-Thank you.
-Keep it coming, okay?
NARRATOR: With entrées
leaving Mia's kitchen
at a steady pace...
GORDON: Keep it going, Mia.
Keep it going.
-This is juicy and soft.
-Yeah.
NARRATOR: Over in the red
kitchen, veteran Ariel...
Guys, next ticket,
how long chicken, wagyu?
NARRATOR: Is continuing
to push Bret for perfection.
Walking as soon
as garnish is up, Chef.
ARIEL: Thank you.
Bret has a big responsibility.
He only has to cook
two proteins tonight,
so I need to make sure
that he nurses and babysits
that wagyu so that
it's absolutely perfect.
(fire crackling)
Oh, boy.
BRET: I wish I was
in the finale right now,
considering I was so close,
but Ariel--
she's a phenomenal chef,
and she deserves this win bad,
and I'm gonna do whatever I can
to [bleep] help her get it.
Chef, behind, chicken, wagyu.
He told me he walked up
chicken garnish
followed by steak garnish.
GORDON: [bleep] hell.
Really? It's cold.
We're serving
cold [bleep] food.
I need a little heat on this.
-Be very careful.
GORDON: Just touch it.
-I don't want it overcooked.
BRET: Heard, Chef.
I know it's a wagyu,
I get that,
-but it's barely lukewarm.
-Yes, Chef.
Timing's way off.
BRET: I feel bad whenever
I [bleep] up a food
or it's not 100% flawless
the first time
whether it's for Ariel,
Chef, any customer,
my clients, whatever.
I bring passion every time
I step in that kitchen.
BRET: Chef,
right behind to your left.
-ARIEL: Thank you.
-Get this on the plate.
It's got to send.
Service, please.
Let's go, let's go.
-Three pork, one churrasco.
-We got a minute and a half.
NARRATOR: After a few hiccups
from both teams...
Pick up two mackerel,
two wagyu, how long?
-Right now, Chef.
MOTTO: Right now.
NARRATOR:
The Hell's Kitchen rookie...
-Rested?
-Yes, Chef.
NARRATOR: And the
Hell's Kitchen veteran...
-Let's go. Send it up.
-Walking.
NARRATOR: Are now both
pushing out quality entrées
at a brisk pace...
GORDON: Got to go,
Got to go, got to go, got to go.
NARRATOR: And living up
to Chef Ramsay's
high expectations.
GORDON: Very good.
MIA: Perfect.
I'm not sharing this with you.
-This is too good.
MARSHA: Wow, that's great!
That is really good,
you know?
They did a good job.
Oh.
Away now--two sea bass,
two churrasco.
JOSE: Two sea bass--
-I want it perfect, Roe, okay?
ROE: Yes, ma'am.
-How long?
-Five minutes, five minutes.
-Five.
-You need five? That's fine.
-Yeah. Five.
Guys, this is
the last stretch, okay?
-Let's finish strong.
-Push it up.
'Cause I want you guys
to nail it.
We have
a really good pace going,
and it feels good, but I'm not
celebrating just yet.
Two sea bass,
two churrasco, how long?
You ready? I can go.
Do you need a minute?
ROE: I think I'm good.
HEATHER: Okay.
-Chef, coming in to the right.
-Yep.
♪ ♪
-How long on that sea bass?
-In my hand, Chef, walking.
♪ ♪
Is that the best
you can do, Roe?
It's falling apart.
GORDON: Were you boiling
it rapidly or steaming it?
-Steaming it, Chef.
-It looks terrible.
I always have
this problem that the minute
I go under on something,
I, like, overcompensate
on the next and go over.
Refire everything, guys--
garnish, protein, everything.
Heard.
For some unknown reason,
which I don't understand why,
Roe was the first pick
last night,
and I don't know if those
are big shoes to fill or what,
but she's dropping the ball.
How long for table four
to come out,
the main course,
more or less?
We're refiring it,
everything fresh.
-Okay. Perfect.
-So I'd rather be a bit slower
and perfect
than send something
that she's not happy with,
right?
-Okay, perfect.
-Piss off.
How long--two sea bass,
two churrasco?
Protein's walking.
-How long, sea bass?
TREV: Sea bass?
♪ ♪
It's okay?
ROE: For the love of God.
HEATHER:
You good, Roe?
-Are you happy with that?
MIA: Yes.
-Yes, I'm happy with that.
-Hallelujah.
-That's what I'm talking about.
Go.
Follow with the broth.
-This is the bass.
-Oh, my God.
All right, listen up,
I'm firing a six-top.
We're almost there, guys.
Keep pushing.
Two mackerel,
two chicken, two wagyu.
-Heard.
-Got it.
ARIEL: Guys, push for me, okay?
MOTTO: Yes, Chef.
Let's do it.
Let's finish strong.
Let's do it, yo.
Come on, yo.
-You guys are smashing this.
-Got you.
Service is going so great.
We're almost there.
We're down
to the last six-top.
-A-team, what, what?
TREV: What?
And let's finish as strong
as we started.
Where are we? Two mackerel,
two chicken, two wagyu?
TREV: How long on the mackerel?
SCOTLEY: 90 seconds.
I'll be there in 2 1/2
as long as garnish is ready.
This six-top
are the executives
from the Six Flags
Magic Mountain,
and I think they looked
after you last night, right?
ALL: Yes, Chef.
-Yes.
Let's go. I'm taking
your garnish on there.
Heard.
I'm bringing it right to you.
-Hot behind.
-Okay.
Look, hit me with some
vinegar here.
Come on, A-Team.
KANAE: A-Team.
♪ ♪
Hey, Scotley, that mackerel
is sexy, all right?
-Nice job.
-[smooches] For you, baby.
♪ ♪
Bret, can I get
a new chicken refire?
GORDON: How burnt is that skin?
-My fault, Chef. Sorry, Chef.
-The mackerel is cooked.
-Won't happen again, Chef.
Come on, Bret.
We're almost there.
Put your big-boy pants on,
and let's get
this [bleep] rolling.
-Bret, I need that chicken.
-30 seconds.
Let's go.
I don't want to give it
to you raw, Chef.
I [bleep] up with the chicken,
so I got to make sure
that this chicken's proper,
and, yabba dabba doo,
-we keep it moving.
-Bret, chicken?
MOTTO: Come on, Bret.
ARIEL: Let's go, Bret.
The mackerel's
been there two minutes.
BRET: Chicken, hot pan.
ARIEL: It's raw.
GORDON: [bleep]. Bret!
-Yes, Chef?
-Look at me!
-I would be freaking out.
-Wake up!
-I am awake, Chef!
Yeah, well, if you were awake,
you wouldn't be cooking
[bleep] raw chicken!
Wow.
Needles.
Essential for pine trees,
but maybe not for people
with rheumatoid arthritis.
Because there are options.
Like an "Unjection™".
XELJANZ XR.
A once-daily pill
for adults with moderate
to severe RA
for whom methotrexate
did not work well enough.
XELJANZ XR can reduce pain,
swelling
and further joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ XR can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes
fatal infections and cancers,
including lymphoma
have happened.
As have tears in the stomach
or intestines,
serious allergic reactions,
low blood cell counts,
higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels.
Don't start XELJANZ XR
if you have an infection.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before
and while taking XELJANZ XR,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you've been
somewhere fungal infections
are common and if you have had
TB, hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Needles.
Fine for some things.
But for you, one pill a day
may provide symptom relief.
Ask your doctor about
XELJANZ XR.
An "Unjection™".
♪♪
[Cell phone rings]
Where are you?
Well the squirrels
are back in the attic.
Mom?
Your dad won't
call an exterminator...
Can I call
you back, Mom?
He says it's
personal this time...
If you're a mom, you
call at the worst time.
It's what you do.
If you want to save fifteen
percent or more
on car insurance, you
switch to GEICO.
It's what you do.
Where are you?
It's very loud there.
Are you taking a
Zumba class?
Julie means more to
me than anything.
And I wanted to ask you
before I ask her.
May I have your permission,
to marry her?
You're not just marrying her.
You're marrying...
...her whole world.
Get zero-down special financing
on bridal purchases
with the Kay Jewelers
credit card.
♪♪
Here is another Laundry Hack
from Home Made Simple.
Do you want ready to wear
clothing without all the hassle?
You can, with Bounce Dryer
sheets.
Simply toss two sheets in the
dryer to iron less.
We dried one shirt without
Bounce,
and an identical shirt using
Bounce.
The Bounce shirt has fewer
wrinkles, less static,
and more softness and
freshness.
For extra large or wrinkly
loads, toss in three sheets.
Dermatologist tested Bounce Free
and Gentle
is free of dyes and perfumes.
Bounce out wrinkles, Bounce out
static.
(dramatic music)
Look at me!
-Wake up!
-I am awake, Chef!
Yeah, well, if you were awake,
you wouldn't be cooking
[bleep] raw chicken!
-Heard, Chef--
-Wake up a bit [bleep] more.
Enough's enough.
-Bret, come here, please.
-Still a little under?
That's why I didn't want
to serve it to you.
Yep, take that one.
Take that one.
Heard. Come on. If that one is,
then that one is.
Actually, both of them, yep.
Just give it two more minutes,
all right, Bret?
Heard, Chef.
We're so close
to the end of service.
We so don't have time
for these mistakes.
GORDON: Come on, Brett.
-I got it, Chef.
I'm finishing the steaks,
and I'm going.
Third [bleep] time.
We have to get
this food out right.
Very hot pan, very hot pan.
♪ ♪
Hey, Bret, your chicken
looks beautiful. Thank you.
-Thank you, Chef.
-Ariel, good job. Well done.
NARRATOR: With Bret finally
delivering perfect chicken...
-Last ticket of the night.
NARRATOR: Both Ariel and Mia
are pushing their brigades
toward the finish line.
MIA: Two chicken, two pork--
how long?
ROE: I need three minutes
in the oven.
JOSE: Two minutes.
-Nail it.
-Got it.
-Let's bring it home, guys.
Come on, guys, push it.
Guys, I need perfect food
on this table.
Let's go. Come on, y'all.
Finish strong for Ariel, man.
Two chicken, two pork--
how long?
I'm ready to go
in one minute, Chef.
-Pork, how long?
ROE: One minute for the pork.
-Taste it. I want it perfect.
GORDON: Keep it going. Good.
This is the last table.
Send it to me.
BRET: Ready to go.
Can I walk these steaks?
MOTTO: Yes, Chef.
I got two mackerel.
Chef, going in
to your right really hot.
ROE: Walking pork hot,
very hot, out of the oven.
MIA: Perfect.
Right behind, steaks going
with the two mackerel
right there--
thank you, Chef.
All right, mackerel's good.
Beautiful.
Hold on.
Go, go.
ARIEL: Service, please.
WOMAN: It is really good.
The temperature
is perfect.
-That's amazing, right?
-It melts in your mouth.
This is wonderful.
The detail in the presentation
really goes a long way.
Ladies,
how is everything?
-Oh, my God.
-Thank you.
-It's wonderful, love it.
Love the little general
in you.
Well, you have to be.
You have to be.
-You got to be a general.
-It gets busy, yes.
-A hustle is on point, baby.
-Thank you.
Have a great night.
Thank you very much.
You guys did a great job.
ARIEL:
I love you, too, man.
I am so glad service is over.
I hope Chef Ramsay
saw a true leader tonight,
a captain,
and someone that he can trust.
-Oh, you were so good.
-Thank you.
-It was so amazing.
Hey, I liked that mackerel.
It was pretty good.
You think you can fix that
for me some other time?
-(laughter)
-Huh?
Thank you, guys, so much.
Amazing work, everybody.
Amazing work. Thank you.
We had a few bumps, but
I'm happy and proud of myself.
I left all of it
in the kitchen.
Thank you so much.
I gave everything I had.
(smooches)
(exciting music)
♪ ♪
BRET:
I tried to do my best.
ARIEL:
You did a great job.
-You did a really nice job.
-Thank you.
I feel like it's gonna be a
very, very close call tonight.
I have no hard feelings
against Mia,
but I really hope that Ariel
wins today, seriously.
-Thank you for your work, Jose.
-You're very welcome.
-Thank you so much.
-Mia...
-I told you I got you.
I'm proud of Mia coming in
as a rookie
and proving
to the veterans that,
you know, we were stronger
than what they imagined.
Definitely feel like
Mia's taking this W home.
MIA:
Dinner service was great.
It's over now,
and this is when
the nerves really kick in,
'cause there's absolutely
nothing I can do anymore.
JOSE: Amazing job, both of you.
ARIEL: Thank you.
MIA: Thank you.
Thank you for your work.
BRET:
May the best lady win.
Congratulations
to the both of youse.
I'm proud of my team.
They did an amazing job.
I couldn't have asked
for a better team.
I'm just anxious now.
I can't sit down right now.
I'm wired right now,
[bleep] wired.
I feel relieved
because we got through
the final dinner service.
I think it went pretty well,
and I'm just moments away
from finding out
whether or not
I've won or not,
which is giving me
total anxiety.
TREV: Good job.
Good job.
I'm trying to just keep it
together for a minute.
-You'll be okay.
-I'm good.
♪ ♪
Would anybody like
some ice cream?
HEATHER: No, you're good.
(laughs)
I was like, "That's my dog."
GORDON:
Time to get serious.
-(knocks on door)
-(Heather gasps)
(Kanae gasps)
(gasping dramatically)
Chef Ramsay, what are
you doing here?
-We're doing karaoke later,
and you're gonna sing.
-Jamie, this is your house?
-I know, it's not much,
but it's home.
Right, kids?
-Kids?
-Papa, Papa!
-[ Laughs ]
-You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
-Oh, yeah.
-This one is tiny like a child.
-Yeah, she is.
Oh, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most --
a home and auto bundle
from Progressive.
-Oh, sweetie,
please, play for us.
-Oh, no, I couldn't.
-Please.
-Okay.
[ Singing in Spanish ]
I've hunted every dragon.
-Please.
-Okay.
This is full blown war.
We'll never give them up.
How To Train Your Dragon
the Hidden World
THIS IS A TEST.
FL
[ growl ]
Cute.
Ahh!
Now that's a king.
Right now, you can get two
KFC Chicken Littles for 3 bucks.
It doesn't get any
better then that.
"Frying sound"
"Kapushh"
"Shooo Shoop"
"Shoop"
"Kapah!"
Actually, with four
flavors to choose from,
it did get better,
and I stand corrected.
Get any 2 KFC Chicken
Littles for 3 dollars.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
♪ All the ways, all the ways ♪
♪ Tell me all the ways  ♪
♪ And he said ♪
♪ Girl, you take care of me ♪
♪ You are my therapy ♪
♪ The better half of me ♪
♪ Say it again ♪
♪ If you love me,
love me, love me ♪
♪ Like you say ♪
♪ Darling tell me all the ways ♪
♪ Tell me all the ways ♪
Now, we're bringing
you all the ways
to get what you need.
Target Run & Done.
Your favorite restaurants now
deliver with DoorDash.
♪
It doesn't matter
where you are.
♪
It doesn't matter what
you're hungry for.
It doesn't even matter
how many you are.
♪
Restaurants come to you.
Delicious at your door.
Download DoorDash.
First order, no delivery fee.
(dramatic music)
GORDON:
Time to get serious.
-(knock on door)
-(Heather gasps)
-(Kanae gasps)
-So this is where you live?
-Nice.
KANAE: Look, behind you.
GORDON:
Oh, my God.
You got to look at this
all the time?
BRET: Hell, yeah.
HEATHER: Yeah.
I'm not one for apologizing,
but I am sorry about
that [bleep] mess on there.
-(laughter)
JOSE: No, Chef.
First of all,
let me tell our returning chefs
how much I appreciate
the effort
that you all put in
across tonight's service.
Not only did you
support your chefs,
but you guys
had a good service.
ALL:
Thank you, Chef.
ROE: Even after, you know,
being eliminated,
I will bleed for Chef Ramsay.
That's the hierarchy.
That's your mentor.
We got a lot
more things to do,
and I am miles away
from being ready,
but for now,
I'd like both of you to say
good-bye to your brigades...
ALL: Bye, guys.
GORDON: And your sous chefs.
-See you in a little bit?
-Yep.
ARIEL: Thank you.
MIA: Thank you so much
for tonight.
Guys, head
into the dining room.
I'll see you there shortly.
BRET:
Hell, yeah, let's do it.
♪ ♪
GORDON:
Scallops are cooked beautifully.
I love what you did
with the celery root.
You've done something
pretty magical.
-Thank you, Chef.
-Good job.
GORDON:
Just look at that--textbook.
-Thank you, Chef.
-The first recipient
of the black jacket,
congratulations, Ariel.
-Thank you, Chef.
-Great job.
Thank you.
Why do I have tuna? I need two
beef tartare, not tuna tartare.
Look at me. Well spotted.
♪ ♪
It's amazing.
GORDON: I want to get
to the end, and I want more.
-Yes.
MOTTO: Awesome.
You did a really nice job
on the steaming on this fish.
I'll take the rest to go.
This is a delicious dish.
It is worthy of being on a menu
right now in a restaurant.
-Peanut butter.
-Yes!
-Good girl.
-Nice work, Mia.
-Four for four.
-It doesn't look like lobster.
You're absolutely right,
well spotted.
-It is monkfish.
-Yes, Chef.
♪ ♪
MIA: This is it, girl.
ARIEL: (laughing) I know.
This is bananas.
I'm having, like,
an out-of-body experience
right now.
Yeah.
I said in the beginning
I thought Mia
was my biggest competition,
and I think that she overcame
a lot of hurdles,
but I think based
on my performance
that I won "Hell's Kitchen."
Let's get this over with.
I'm gonna beat Ariel
because I feel like
we're at the same level
as far as leadership goes.
I feel like my dishes
are more creative.
So I definitely think
I'm the next executive chef
at the flagship Hell's Kitchen
restaurant in Las Vegas.
-(phone ringing)
-Scared me.
(laughs)
Hi, this is Mia.
GORDON: Hi, Mia.
I've made my decision.
Can you and Ariel please make
your way to my office?
-Yes, Chef.
-Thank you.
He said make our way
to his office.
♪ ♪
MIA: This is it, girl.
(cheers and applause)
MAN: Let's go, Mia!
Let's go, Mia!
(cheers and applause continue)
Right, you two, welcome.
Ariel, Mia, this has been an
extremely difficult decision,
let me tell you.
Mia, never before
have we had a chef
that has performed so strongly
across challenges.
Above that, you've been one
of the most creative chefs
we've ever had
in Hell's Kitchen.
-Thank you, Chef.
-Ariel...
-Yes, Chef?
-You have been
the most consistent chef
across this
entire competition,
so it's no surprise to me
that you are the only chef
on either team
never to be considered
for elimination.
Ariel, right now
how are you feeling?
Ugh, my stomach is in knots,
Chef, to be honest with you.
I'm just trying
to contain myself
and maintain my calm
that I've had all season.
Mia, what's going
through your mind?
My heart is racing,
but I'm just so proud
of what I've accomplished,
and I'm really proud of myself,
and I'm so grateful for all
the faith you've had in me.
I could not be prouder
of the two of you.
In my eyes,
you're both winners.
BOTH:
Thank you, Chef.
Mia and Ariel,
please step up
in front of your doors.
BOTH: Yes, Chef.
♪ ♪
MIA: For me,
everything is on the line.
This is what I want.
I've been
completely sure of myself.
I came to this competition
to get here.
This is it.
ARIEL:
This is a huge opportunity.
This is the perfect
next place for me to be.
It just feels so right
that if it doesn't happen,
I'm just gonna be so confused
and just so bummed out.
The chef whose door opens
will become the winner
of "Hell's Kitchen"
and the executive chef
of the flagship
Hell's Kitchen restaurant
at Caesars Palace Las Vegas,
with a salary
of $1/4 million dollars.
♪ ♪
Both of you very carefully
place your hand
on top of your door handle.
♪ ♪
On the count of three,
I want you
to turn your handles.
♪ ♪
One, two...
Three.
(cheers and applause)
Ahhh...
Boommm!
Wow!
Lemme ask you a question,
who is the play-maker of this
new Big Mac with Bacon?
It's the crispy
bacon, of course.
The flavor brings a whole
new dimension to the game.
Bacon does not
win championships.
Special Sauce wins
championships, my friend!
You're wrong.
And I'm a doctor.
Which means I'm
always right.
I'm gonna get a second
opinion, from my mouth.
McDonald's Classics with
Bacon, only for a limited time.
Is it the best thing to
happen to our Classics?
Or to bacon?
Try r yourself
and decide.
This Valentine's Day,
give her your heart.
Or, ask her for her hand.
Save 25% off everything.
Plus, enjoy specials
like these diamond earrings
for just $59.
Only through February 11th.
At Zales. The Diamond Store.
♪ ♪
♪ Step it up. ♪
♪ Always take the risk. ♪
Don't just watch it...
Put your phone down and do it.
♪ Drip splash like the ice
on the wrist. ♪
♪ Brrt brrt brrt brrt ♪
♪ that's a call I can't miss. ♪
Let's do.
Sweat.
Dedication.
Cupcakes.
I'm Michael Griffin.
I'm Brian Orakpo.
We played football together for
the Titans.
Now, we own a cupcake shop.
We bake, we decorate.
I love this new Surface Pro.
It's light, it's sleek, it's
fast.
I'm able to draw what color
frosting we want.
We do a lot with social media.
We have funny videos that we do
in the bakery [laughs].
There's nothing that you can't
do on this device.
Cupcakes are a great business.
Oh yeah, as long as you don't
eat the profits!
(dramatic music)
The chef whose door opens
will become the executive chef
of the flagship
Hell's Kitchen restaurant
at Caesars Palace Las Vegas,
with a salary
of $1/4 million dollars.
Good luck.
On the count of three, I want
you to turn your handles.
One, two...
♪ ♪
Three.
(cheers and applause)
MAN: [bleep], yeah!
(cheers and applause continue)
Yes! Yes! Yes!
♪ ♪
Mia...
Thank you, Chef.
That was amazing.
Well done.
Thank you, Chef.
You're gonna have
a phenomenal career.
-Thank you so much, Chef.
-No doubt, okay?
Thank you for the opportunity.
I'm so proud to have gotten
to this place as a rookie.
You know, I knocked out
everybody but one,
and this isn't the end for me.
Like, this is
just the beginning.
-(cheers and applause)
-MAN: Yeah!
I have been to Hell's Kitchen
twice and made it out alive,
and not only alive,
but I made it out a winner,
and this feels incredible
right now.
(cheers and applause continue)
Um... (laughs)
-Great job.
-Thank you.
Come on.
Go down those stairs.
They'd like to see you.
Come on.
(cheers and applause continue)
Let's go.
MAN:
A-team! A-team! A-team!
Oh, [bleep]!
This job is made for me.
I am the person who says every
single day when I go to bed,
"How am I gonna be better
than I was yesterday?"
(sobbing)
Thank you.
ARIEL: I dedicate winning
to both my parents.
I'm happy to show my parents
how far I've come.
Every time they see me succeed,
it makes them feel happy.
Mia, I have so much
respect for you.
I think that you
are so talented,
and when I go to Las Vegas,
if you want to come,
if I have the position
for you, it's yours.
I would hire you
in a heartbeat.
Would you like to hear from
the "Hell's Kitchen" winner?
ALL: Yes!
Come on.
I am so [bleep]
excited right now.
(laughs) I'm sorry.
I am so excited to work
with this incredible woman
right here, Chef Christina.
I can't wait to work for you.
I can't wait to work with you,
Chef Jocky,
and of course, Chef,
I am very excited to show you
-what I have in store, so...
-Cannot wait.
Thank you
for this opportunity.
Incredible,
amazing, thank you.
Wow.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our "Hell's Kitchen"
winner, Ariel!
(cheers and applause)
GORDON: Since the first time
she was here,
Ariel has grown tenfold
as a chef.
She is fiercely talented,
extremely determined,
and a commanding leader.
I could not be more pleased
to have her
as my executive chef
of Hell's Kitchen in Las Vegas.
One final thing to do--
it's a tradition here
in Hell's Kitchen.
Hang that up.
-We got it?
-Get it on there?
I don't know.
It's up to you.
Come on, carpenter,
straighten that out.
(laughs)
-Yay.
-Well done.
ARIEL:
To feel like you did well
and to know
that you earned something
and that you belong there
is an amazing feeling.
WOMAN: A-team!
This has been the most
rewarding journey
of my entire life.
I have worked so hard
in my career,
and to just be
so validated right now
for everything
that I have ever done
is the most satisfying feeling
I have ever felt.
-Cheers!
-Yeah, one big clink, cheers.
MAN: Cheers!
Hell's Kitchen.
-Cheers.
-Whoo! Season 18.
Season 18.
Announcer:  Wednesday, Gordon
heads to Hollyood to save a
struggling restaurant on a new
24 Hours to Hell and Back.
>>> RIGHT NOW AT 10:00.
A SECOND WOMAN IS ACCUSING
VIRGINIA'S LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR
OF RAPE.
THIS, AS THE GOVERNOR DOUBLED
DOWN ON HIS REFUSAL TO