e:
WE'RE THE HISTORY DETECTIVES,
AND WE'RE GOING TO INVESTIGATE
SOME UNTOLD STORIES
FROM AMERICA'S PAST.
THIS WEEK, IS THIS
A MISSING MURDER WEAPON
FROM THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY
MASSACRE?
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SHOOT IT?
Tukufu:
DID THE FATHER
OF JOHN WILKES BOOTH
THREATEN TO ASSASSINATE
A SITTING PRESIDENT?
SOMEONE HAS WRITTEN
"ANONYMOUS."
IS IT BY JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
OR NOT?
THERE'S NO QUESTION, JUNIUS
BRUTUS BOOTH WAS INSANE.
Wes:
DID THIS METAL BOMB EXPLODE
A MORBID BLACK MARKET TRADE
IN 19th-CENTURY OHIO?
FIRE IN THE HOLE!
Elvis Costello:
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ I GET SO ANGRY
WHEN THE TEARDROPS START ♪
♪ BUT HE CAN'T BE WOUNDED
'CAUSE HE'S GOT NO HEART ♪
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ IT'S JUST LIKE
WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
Gwendolyn:
THIS PROGRAM WAS MADE POSSIBLE
BY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO YOUR PBS STATION
FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.
Elyse:
OUR FIRST STORY
INVESTIGATES A WEAPON
THAT MAY HAVE BEEN FIRED
IN ONE OF THE NATION'S
MOST INFAMOUS CRIMES.
FEBRUARY 14, 1929,
ST. VALENTINE'S DAY:
GANGSTERS TURN A DAY
OF LOVE AND REFLECTION
INTO A BLOODBATH,
EXECUTING SEVEN MEN
IN A CHICAGO GARAGE.
[ machine gun firing ]
AUTHORITIES SUSPECT THE HAND
OF POWERFUL GANGSTER AL CAPONE,
WHO WAS FIGHTING TO CONTROL THE
CITY'S ILLEGAL LIQUOR TRADE.
THE DAYLIGHT KILLING
OUTRAGES THE NATION
AND BECOMES A SYMBOL
OF THE FAILURE OF PROHIBITION.
HOWEVER, NO ONE IS EVER
CONVICTED OF THE KILLING
AND THE CRIME
REMAINS UNSOLVED.
NOW MIKE LUX
OF LAKE GENEVA, WISCONSIN,
BELIEVES HE HAS
THE MISSING WEAPON
FROM THIS LEGENDARY
GANGLAND MASSACRE.
THIS GUN MAY HAVE TAKEN
THE LIVES OF TWO MEN.
I'M ON MY WAY TO MEET MIKE
AND LOOK INTO HIS STORY.
VERY NICE TO MEET YOU.
OH, WOW!
12-GAUGE SHOTGUN.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT IT.
AND WHAT'S THE STORY BEHIND IT?
IT WAS SUPPOSEDLY USED IN THE
ST. VALENTINE'S DAY MASSACRE.
THAT WAS IN CHICAGO
IN 1929.
YES.
YOU KNOW, JUST BY LOOKING
AT THE GUN,
TO ME IT KIND OF LOOKS
LIKE THE BARREL
IS NOT PERIOD TO THE PIECE.
CORRECT.
I HAD THIS BARREL PUT ON
TO MAKE IT LEGAL.
ORIGINALLY THE BARREL WAS CUT
OFF PROBABLY ABOUT RIGHT HERE.
AND I ACTUALLY HAVE
A COUPLE PICTURES OF IT.
OH, AND I CAN SEE
THE BARREL'S MUCH SHORTER.
MIKE TELLS ME THAT
SHORT-BARREL SHOTGUNS
ARE FEDERALLY REGULATED
AND THAT HE PUT A LONGER BARREL
ON THE GUN
TO COMPLY WITH THESE RULES.
HOW'D YOU GET THE GUN?
I HAD INHERITED IT FROM
MY FATHER WHEN HE PASSED AWAY.
MIKE SAYS HIS FATHER
GOT THE GUN
FROM A FORMER CHICAGO FIRE
COMMISSIONER, ROBERT QUINN.
MIKE BELIEVES THAT QUINN,
WHO IS NOW DECEASED,
MAY HAVE USED HIS INFLUENCE
TO SECRETLY ACQUIRE THE GUN.
I THINK WHEN QUINN
ACQUIRED IT,
IT HAD TO HAVE BEEN
IN THE MID-'70s.
MIKE'S FATHER WAS KILLED
IN AN AIR CRASH IN 1979.
TWO DAYS LATER, ONE OF
HIS FRIENDS TALKED TO ME,
AND HE WAS VERY UPSET
ABOUT THE PLANE CRASH,
BUT HE WAS ALSO VERY WORRIED
THAT NOW I OWN THIS PIECE
AND HE DIDN'T WANT ME
TO BE SHOWING IT OFF
OR TELLING ANYBODY ABOUT IT,
AND I HAVEN'T.
THAT'S WHY I'VE HAD IT
FOR 30 YEARS HIDDEN AWAY.
WHAT'D YOU THINK WHEN YOUR DAD
TOLD YOU THAT THIS WAS USED
IN THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY
MASSACRE?
I THOUGHT, "COME ON,
YOU'RE PULLING MY LEG."
AND HE WAS DEAD SERIOUS.
AND HE WAS A SERIOUS
KIND OF GUY.
WHEN IT CAME TO WEAPONS
LIKE THIS IN HIS COLLECTION,
HE WAS NOT FOOLING.
MIKE, WHAT EXACTLY
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW?
IF IT TRULY IS THE SHOTGUN
THAT WAS USED
AT THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY
MASSACRE.
I WILL SEE WHAT I CAN
FIND OUT.
DO YOU MIND IF I SIT HERE
FOR A WHILE AND EVALUATE IT?
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I USED TO WORK IN THE GUN
DEPARTMENT AT CHRISTIE'S,
SO I KNOW A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT GUNS.
AND THE FIRST THING
I NEED TO DETERMINE
WAS IF THIS GUN
WAS EVEN AROUND IN 1929.
WAS IT PERIOD TO THE TIME
OF THE MASSACRE?
IT CERTAINLY APPEARS TO BE.
THE WOODEN FORESTOCK
IS FOR A REPEATING,
OR PUMP-ACTION,
SHOTGUN.
THAT MEANS IT CAN FIRE
MULTIPLE SHOTS
WITHOUT RELOADING.
I KNOW THAT THERE IS
A SERIAL NUMBER HERE.
AH, HERE IT IS:
18514 B.
THAT MAY HELP US
MORE PRECISELY DATE THE GUN,
ALTHOUGH BACK THEN
I'M PRETTY CERTAIN A PURCHASER
WAS NOT REQUIRED
TO REGISTER THEIR WEAPON.
I SEE THAT IT SAYS
"WESTERN FIELD" ON THE PLATE.
YOU KNOW, I DID NOTICE SOMETHING
UNUSUAL OVER HERE ON THE STOCK.
THERE ARE TWO NOTCHES.
MAYBE WE COULD GET SOME
INFORMATION FROM THAT AS WELL.
IF THIS GUN REALLY WAS USED
IN THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY
MASSACRE,
THEN IT'S AN EXCEPTIONAL PIECE
OF HISTORY
AND ITS COLLECTION VALUE
WOULD BE VERY HIGH.
ON THE MORNING
OF FEBRUARY 14, 1929,
SEVEN IMMACULATELY DRESSED MEN
GATHERED IN A GARAGE
ON CHICAGO'S NORTH SIDE.
SOME WERE MEMBERS
OF A GANG
LED BY THE NOTORIOUS BOOTLEGGER
BUGS MORAN.
WITHOUT WARNING,
GUNMEN STORMED IN
AND UNLEASHED A HAIL OF BULLETS
THAT LEFT ALL SEVEN DEAD.
WITNESSES REPORTED SEEING
WHAT LOOKED LIKE TWO POLICE
OFFICERS LEAVE THE GARAGE.
THE MID-MORNING SLAUGHTER
TURNED THE MEDIA SPOTLIGHT
ON THE CITY OF CHICAGO AND THE
VIOLENT STRUGGLE BEING WAGED
OVER CONTROL
OF THE ILLEGAL LIQUOR TRADE.
I'M IN CHICAGO TO MEET
THE AUTHOR OF THIS BOOK,
ART BILEK.
HI, ART.
HERE IS THE GUN.
TELL ME YOUR OPINION ON THAT.
WHAT DO I HAVE HERE?
IT'S A 12-GAUGE SHOTGUN...
ART IS ALSO
A FORMER POLICE OFFICER
AND FAMILIAR WITH THE WEAPONS
OF CHOICE OF CRIMINALS.
MOST IMPORTANTLY,
IT HAS A SAWED-OFF STOCK.
GANGSTERS IN THE 1920s
HAD THESE STOCKS MODIFIED
SO THAT THEY COULD CARRY THESE
UNDER THEIR OVERCOATS LIKE THIS.
SO IT'S A GANGSTER GUN?
OH, YES.
IN FACT, THAT'S THE WAY I WOULD
REFER TO IT, AS A GANGSTER GUN.
ART SAYS EXACTLY HOW
THE VICTIMS
WERE LURED TO THEIR DEATH
WAS NEVER ESTABLISHED.
INVESTIGATORS SUSPECTED
THE PHONY POLICEMEN
WERE AL CAPONE GANG MEMBERS.
WHEN THEY ORDERED
THE RIVAL GANGSTERS
TO LINE UP AND TURN AROUND,
MORE CAPONE MEN ENTERED,
CARRYING WEAPONS.
WE DON'T KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT WENT ON
EXCEPT TWO OF THE MEN PULLED OUT
THOMPSON SUBMACHINE GUNS
AND BEGAN RIDDLING THE BACK
OF THESE SEVEN MEN
WITH MACHINE GUN BULLETS.
GETTING INFORMATION ABOUT THE
CRIME WAS ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE.
THE CHICAGO UNDERWORLD
WAS RULED BY FEAR.
BEFORE DYING, ONE OF
THE VICTIMS, FRANK GUSENBERG,
TOLD INCREDULOUS POLICE,
"NOBODY SHOT ME."
INVESTIGATORS TURNED
TO EVIDENCE
FROM THE BLOOD-DRENCHED GARAGE.
SERGEANT JAMES LOFTUS, WHO WAS
THE FIRST OFFICER ON THE SCENE,
WAS ABLE TO COLLECT FROM
THE SCENE SEVERAL ITEMS.
HERE IS A COPY
OF THE INVENTORY REPORT
THAT HE FILED THAT VERY DAY.
THERE WERE SEVERAL .45-CALIBER
SHELLS AND BULLETS,
THE SIZE OF AMMUNITION USED
IN THE TOMMY GUN.
ART POINTS OUT SOMETHING
OF PARTICULAR INTEREST.
AND THERE IS THE ITEM
RIGHT THERE:
TWO SHOTGUN SHELLS, 12-GAUGE.
THAT'S THE SAME GAUGE
AS MIKE'S GUN.
I TELL ART THAT MIKE BELIEVES
HIS WEAPON ONCE BELONGED
TO ROBERT QUINN, A FORMER
CHICAGO FIRE COMMISSIONER
IN THE 1950s
THROUGH THE 1970s.
HE WAS ONE OF THE MORE NOTABLE
FIRE COMMISSIONERS
IN THE HISTORY OF CHICAGO.
HE SAYS QUINN WAS PART OF AN
INNER CIRCLE AROUND THE MAYOR
IN A PERIOD
WHEN CONTROL OF EVIDENCE,
ESPECIALLY FOR
A CELEBRATED COLD CASE,
WAS NOT NEARLY
AS TIGHTLY HELD AS TODAY.
DO YOU THINK THAT HE COULD
HAVE OWNED THIS GUN?
HE KNEW ALL OF
THE TOP OFFICIALS.
HE WOULD HAVE KNOWN
THE CORONER VERY WELL.
AND HE WOULD HAVE KNOWN OTHER
PEOPLE IN THE POLICE DEPARTMENT.
IT'S ENTIRELY POSSIBLE
THAT ONE WAY OR ANOTHER
HE MIGHT HAVE MET A MAN
THAT HAD POSSESSION OF THIS GUN.
ART SAYS THE DESCRIPTION
OF TWO OF THE KILLERS
DRESSED IN POLICE UNIFORMS
TURNED UP THE HEAT
ON INVESTIGATORS,
BUT IT WASN'T UNTIL TEN MONTHS
LATER THAT THEY CAUGHT A BREAK:
AN AL CAPONE ASSOCIATE
NAMED FRED "KILLER" BURKE
WAS INVOLVED IN A FENDER BENDER
ACROSS STATE LINES IN MICHIGAN.
WELL, THERE WAS A POLICE OFFICER
ON THE NEXT CORNER,
AND HE BEGAN WALKING DOWN.
WITH THAT, KILLER BURKE
DRIVES OFF,
THE POLICEMAN JUMPS
ON THE RUNNING BOARD,
BURKE TAKES OUT HIS GUN
AND SHOOTS HIM.
THE OFFICER TUMBLES
TO THE GROUND DEAD.
A HUGE MANHUNT FOLLOWS,
AND THAT'S HOW THEY FOUND
BURKE'S CAR OVERTURNED
WHERE HE TRIED TO MAKE
A TURN IN THE ROAD AND FAILED.
ART EXPLAINS THAT BURKE WAS
A CAREER GANGSTER AND HIT MAN.
A WORLD WAR I VET, HE WAS
SUSPECTED OF INTRODUCING
THE THOMPSON SUBMACHINE GUN
TO THE DETROIT MOB,
HELPING MURDER THREE MEN
IN 1927.
IN THE AFTERMATH OF THE
ST. VALENTINE'S DAY KILLINGS,
BURKE WAS HOLED UP
IN A SMALL MICHIGAN TOWN.
AFTER KILLING THE OFFICER,
POLICE RAIDED HIS HIDEOUT.
AND UPSTAIRS ON THE SECOND
FLOOR, THEY OPENED A CLOSET
AND THERE WERE THE TWO
MACHINE GUNS, A SHOTGUN,
AND SOME OTHER
ARMORY-TYPE DEVICES.
FORENSIC ANALYSIS
WOULD LATER CONNECT
SOME OF FRED BURKE'S WEAPONS
TO THE MASSACRE.
WHERE ARE THOSE GUNS NOW?
THE GUNS AT THE CURRENT TIME
ARE BEING HELD
BY THE BERRIEN COUNTY, MICHIGAN,
SHERIFF'S OFFICE,
WHERE THEY WERE RECOVERED
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I'M IN BERRIEN COUNTY TO MEET
WITH LIEUTENANT KEITH HAFER,
THE WEAPONS EXPERT IN CHARGE
OF THE MASSACRE GUNS.
WOW.
THESE ARE THE TWO THOMPSON
SUBMACHINE GUNS USED
IN THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY
MASSACRE.
LIEUTENANT HAFER EXPLAINS
THAT FOR YEARS,
THE GUNS WERE HELD
BY THE FBI
AT THEIR BALLISTICS CRIME LAB
IN QUANTICO, VIRGINIA.
IN THE LATE 1970s, A MICHIGAN
DETECTIVE TRAINING WITH THE FBI
SPOTTED THE GUNS
AND ASKED FOR THEIR RETURN.
ARE THESE THE ONLY GUNS
THAT YOU HAVE?
THERE WERE OTHER GUNS SEIZED
FROM FRED BURKE'S HOME,
BUT THOSE GUNS ARE LONG GONE
AND I HAVE NO RECORD OF THEM.
WELL, I'M INVESTIGATING
THIS SHOTGUN
THAT I BELIEVE MAY HAVE BEEN
USED AT THE MASSACRE.
IT'S CERTAINLY THE RIGHT AGE
AND IT LOOKS LIKE
A GANGSTER GUN.
WHAT I NOTICE IMMEDIATELY
ARE THESE TWO NOTCHES
CUT INTO THE PISTOL GRIP
OF THIS SHOTGUN.
LIEUTENANT HAFER SAYS
CRIMINALS SOMETIMES CARVED
NOTCHES ON THEIR WEAPONS
WHEN THEY KILLED A MAN.
AND THE THOMPSONS
THAT WE HAVE
HAVE NOTCHES CARVED
INTO THE TRIGGER GUARDS.
HE'S NOT SURE
IF THE MARKINGS
CAN CONNECT OUR GUN
TO THE MASSACRE,
BUT OFFERS TO TAKE ME
TO THE FIRING RANGE
TO SHOW EXACTLY WHY OUR GUN
AND THE TOMMY GUN
WOULD HAVE BEEN FAVORITE
GANGSTER WEAPONS.
FIRE!
HIT HIM RIGHT IN THE CHEST,
KEEP GOING.
THE TOMMY GUN
CAN FIRE CONTINUOUSLY.
LIEUTENANT HAFER HAS TOLD ME TO
FIRE JUST THREE SHOTS AT A TIME
BECAUSE THE WEAPON
IS DIFFICULT TO CONTROL.
IT'S PRETTY POWERFUL.
LIEUTENANT HAFER SAYS
THIS MODEL TOMMY GUN
COULD UNLOAD A DEVASTATING
700 ROUNDS A MINUTE.
I CAN UNDERSTAND WHY
A GANGSTER LIKES THAT GUN.
IT WAS THE HIGH-TECH WEAPON
OF ITS DAY.
HE TELLS ME THAT BEFORE THE
INTRODUCTION OF THE TOMMY GUN
TO THE CHICAGO CRIME WORLD
IN 1924,
THE REPEATING SHOTGUN WAS
THE GANGSTER GUN OF CHOICE.
WHAT YOU HAVE HERE IS
A PUMP-ACTION REPEATING SHOTGUN,
WHICH WAS A VERY COMMON AND
DEVASTATING WEAPON OF THE TIME.
OUR GUN IS CAPABLE OF FIRING
SIX SHOTS BEFORE RELOADING,
UNLEASHING A DEVASTATING SPRAY
OF SHOTGUN PELLETS.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SHOOT IT?
YEAH, DEFINITELY.
PULL IT IN TIGHT,
YEP.
AIM AT YOUR TARGET
AND SHOOT WHEN READY.
[ gunshots and reloading ]
WOW, THAT'S GOT QUITE
A KICK TO IT.
WHY DON'T YOU OPEN THE BOLT
AND LET'S MAKE SURE IT'S EMPTY.
OKAY.
NOW, DO YOU THINK
THAT THIS GUN WAS USED
IN THE ST. VALENTINE MASSACRE?
IT'S CERTAINLY A POSSIBILITY.
LIEUTENANT HAFER SUGGESTS
I PICK UP THE SHELL CASINGS.
IF OUR GUN WAS USED
IN THE MASSACRE,
THE SHELLS MAY BEAR
USEFUL FORENSIC INFORMATION.
HE'S NOT SURE WHAT REMAINS
IN THE OLD POLICE FILES
BUT SUGGESTS I SPEAK WITH
POLICE HISTORIAN CHRISS LYON
AT THE HERITAGE MUSEUM AND
CULTURAL CENTER IN ST. JOSEPH.
HI, CHRISS.
HI, ELYSE.
GREAT TO MEET YOU,
WELCOME TO ST. JOSEPH, MICHIGAN.
THANK YOU.
CHRISS SAYS THE POLICE FOUND A
TROVE OF INCRIMINATING EVIDENCE
WHEN THEY RAIDED
FRED BURKE'S HIDEOUT.
THIS ONE IS ONE
OF THE ORIGINAL PHOTOS
OF SOME OF THE WEAPONRY
THAT WAS FOUND
IN FRED BURKE'S HOUSE.
OKAY, SO I SEE HERE
THE TWO TOMMY GUNS
THAT WERE FOUND IN HIS HOUSE.
AND THIS IS ALL THE ARSENAL.
AND THIS MUST BE THE SHOTGUN.
CHRISS EXPLAINS HOW THE CHICAGO
AUTHORITIES HAD TURNED
TO A FORENSICS EXPERT
NAMED CALVIN GODDARD
TO EXAMINE THE BURKE WEAPONS.
WHEN GODDARD TOOK THESE GUNS
TO BE TESTED BALLISTICALLY,
HE TOOK THE TOMMY GUNS
AND HE TOOK THIS GUN,
WHICH IS A 20-GAUGE.
NOW, WE KNOW THAT THERE
WAS A 12-GAUGE USED
IN THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY
MASSACRE
BY THE SHELLS THAT WERE FOUND.
SO IF THIS GUN WASN'T USED
IN THE MASSACRE,
THEN IT'S STILL POSSIBLE
THAT OUR GUN WAS.
I'M CURIOUS, HAD GODDARD ALSO
EXAMINED THE 12-GAUGE SHELLS
FOUND AT THE CRIME SCENE
AFTER THE MASSACRE?
CHRISS SUGGESTS
I SPEAK WITH
FORMER CRIME LAB DIRECTOR
PAUL DOUGHERTY,
WHO HAS STUDIED THE MASSACRE
AND THE SUBSEQUENT
POLICE DETECTIVE WORK.
OKAY, SO HERE'S THE GUN
I TALKED TO YOU ABOUT.
YES.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THIS IS A WESTERN FIELD,
WHICH IS MADE BY STEVENS.
IT HAS A FAIRLY LOW
SERIAL NUMBER,
WHICH INDICATES
IT'S FAIRLY OLD.
PAUL SAYS THE MODEL WAS IN
PRODUCTION FROM 1905 TO 1932
AND PERIOD TO THE MASSACRE.
HOWEVER, HE CAN'T PRECISELY
DATE THE GUN
BECAUSE THE MANUFACTURER'S
SERIAL RECORDS
HAVE BEEN DESTROYED.
SO TELL ME A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT GODDARD.
WELL, CALVIN GODDARD
WAS A FIRST-CLASS SCIENTIST
AND HE APPROACHED EVERYTHING
THAT HE DID AS A SCIENTIST.
PAUL SAYS GODDARD TRAINED
AS A PHYSICIAN,
BUT IN 1926, ENTERED
THE EMERGING FIELD
OF BALLISTIC SCIENCE.
HIS FORENSIC WORK,
WHICH HELPED CONVICT
ANARCHIST NICOLA SACCO
IN THE CELEBRATED SACCO
AND VANZETTI MURDER CASE,
CAUGHT THE ATTENTION
OF THE CHICAGO CORONER.
IT WAS THE ENORMITY OF
THE ST. VALENTINE'S DAY MASSACRE
THAT BROUGHT THE NEED
FOR SCIENTIFIC CRIME DETECTION
TO THE PUBLIC ATTENTION
AND TO THE ATTENTION
OF AUTHORITIES OF CHICAGO.
GODDARD TEST-FIRED
THE BURKE RAID TOMMY GUNS
AND COMPARED THE SHELLS
TO THOSE
FROM THE SCENE OF THE CRIME.
HE EXPLAINED TO
THE CHICAGO INVESTIGATORS
HOW SPENT SHELLS HAD
THEIR OWN IDENTIFYING MARKS.
HE WOULD PUT THE CARTRIDGE CASES
UNDER THE COMPARISON MICROSCOPE,
ONE ON EITHER SIDE.
THEN HE COMPARED THEM
THROUGH THE EYEPIECE,
WHICH IS HERE.
SO, PAUL, TELL ME
WHAT I'M LOOKING AT.
USING A REPLICA
OF GODDARD'S MICROSCOPE,
PAUL TELLS ME TO COMPARE
THE IMPRESSIONS ON TWO SHELLS
FROM GODDARD'S
PERSONAL COLLECTION.
SO THE FIRING PIN IMPRESSIONS
ARE THE SAME.
BY MATCHING
FIRING PIN IMPRESSIONS,
GODDARD DETERMINED THAT
FRED BURKE'S TOMMY GUNS
WERE USED IN THE MASSACRE.
SO THESE CAME
FROM THE SAME GUN.
WELL, I HAVE THESE SHELLS,
AND I SHOT THESE SHELLS
FROM MIKE'S GUN.
PAUL OFFERS TO TAKE
A CLOSER LOOK.
ALTHOUGH THE CARTRIDGE SHELLS
FROM THE CRIME SCENE
ARE LONG GONE, HE SAYS
GODDARD DID EXAMINE THEM
AND TESTIFIED IN FRONT
OF THE CORONER'S GRAND JURY.
THE CHARACTERISTICS
THAT GODDARD EMPHASIZED
IN HIS TESTIMONY, THOUGH,
WERE THE EXTRACTOR
AND EJECTOR MARKS.
EXTRACTOR MARKS ARE
THE MARKINGS THAT OCCUR
WHEN A SHELL IS
IN THE CHAMBER OF A GUN
AND IS EXTRACTED
FROM THE CHAMBER,
AND AN EJECTOR MARKING OCCURS
WHEN THE SHELL IS KICKED OUT
OF THE GUN.
WE TAKE A CLOSE LOOK
AT OUR SHELLS.
OH, THOSE TWO LITTLE SCRATCHES?
THAT IS CORRECT.
I SEE THEM.
WHAT PAUL TELLS ME NEXT
IS CERTAINLY GOING TO BE
OF INTEREST TO MIKE.
INVESTIGATORS FOUND
BULLETS AND SHELLS
AT THE SCENE OF THE CRIME,
AND TWO OF THOSE SHELLS
WERE FROM A 12-GAUGE SHOTGUN,
THE SAME GAUGE
AS YOUR SHOTGUN.
THAT GETS US VERY CLOSE.
I TELL MIKE THAT THE STRANGE
CARVED NOTCHES ON HIS WEAPON
COULD HAVE BEEN
A GANGSTER SIGNATURE,
INDICATING THE WEAPON
HAD BEEN USED IN A MURDER.
SIMILAR MARKINGS
HAD ALSO BEEN SEEN
ON THE THOMPSON SUBMACHINE GUNS
USED IN THE MASSACRE.
ALTHOUGH MISSING EVIDENCE
MADE A DIRECT COMPARISON
WITH HIS SHELLS
IMPOSSIBLE TODAY,
AT THE TIME OF THE MASSACRE,
THE EXPERT BROUGHT IN
BY THE AUTHORITIES
HAD CONDUCTED A THOROUGH
FORENSIC INVESTIGATION.
GODDARD DID CLOSELY EXAMINE
THE SHELLS THAT WERE FOUND
AT THE SCENE OF THE CRIME,
AND HE MADE A PRETTY
INTERESTING DISCOVERY.
THESE ARE THE TYPES
OF MARKINGS
THAT GODDARD FOUND ON THE SHELLS
FROM THE SCENE OF THE CRIME.
GODDARD HAD DETERMINED
THAT THE SHOTGUN USED
IN THE MURDER OF SEVEN MEN
ON ST. VALENTINE'S DAY, 1929,
WAS A PUMP-ACTION GUN, TOO,
THE SAME AS MIKE'S.
SO IN YOUR OPINION,
COULD THIS GUN HAVE BEEN USED
IN THE MASSACRE?
YES.
IT IS THE RIGHT VINTAGE.
IT HAS BOTH THE EXTRACTOR
AND EJECTOR MARKINGS
WHICH GODDARD IDENTIFIED.
WE CAN PROVE THAT THE GUN
THAT WAS SHOT THAT DAY
WAS A 12-GAUGE
REPEATING SHOTGUN.
YOUR GUN IS A 12-GAUGE
RIGHT, RIGHT.
THAT'S GREAT.
I TELL MIKE THERE ARE
NO SURVIVING POLICE RECORDS
OF ANY OTHER SHOTGUN
BEING RECOVERED BY POLICE
AND TIED TO THE KILLINGS.
WHILE WE CAN'T CONCLUSIVELY LINK
YOUR GUN TO THE MASSACRE,
NO EVIDENCE RULES IT OUT.
VERY INTERESTING.
SO IF THE ORIGINAL SHELLS
SURFACE,
THEN WE WOULD BE ABLE
TO FINISH GODDARD'S WORK
AND DETERMINE IF YOUR GUN
FIRED THEM.
HOW DO YOU THINK
YOUR FATHER WOULD FEEL,
THE FACT THAT WE'VE COME
THIS FAR?
HE WOULD BE ECSTATIC.
HE WOULD SAY,
"I TOLD YOU SO."
THANK YOU, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
FRED BURKE WAS NEVER CONVICTED
FOR THE MASSACRE.
INSTEAD, HE WAS PUT AWAY
FOR KILLING POLICE OFFICER
CHARLES SKELLY.
CAPONE WAS EVENTUALLY BROUGHT
DOWN ON CHARGES OF TAX EVASION.
BUT GODDARD'S WORK
BROUGHT CREDIBILITY
TO THE YOUNG FIELD
OF BALLISTICS.
HE WAS GIVEN RESOURCES
TO OPEN
ONE OF THE NATION'S FIRST
INDEPENDENT CRIME LABS
AND CONTINUED TO PIONEER
TECHNIQUES
THAT ARE STILL USED TODAY.
FOR MORE OF MY INTERVIEW
WITH ART BELIK,
VISIT HISTORY DETECTIVES
ON THE WEB AT pbs.org.
THE GUN THAT MADE
THE '20s ROAR
WAS INSPIRED BY WORLD WAR I
TRENCH WARFARE.
THE THOMPSON SUBMACHINE GUN
WAS DESIGNED
BY RETIRED GENERAL
JOHN THOMPSON.
EARLY MACHINE GUNS
WERE EXTREMELY HEAVY
AND TOOK SEVERAL MEN
TO OPERATE.
THOMPSON'S SOLUTION WAS
A RAPID-FIRING WEAPON
OPERATED BY
A SINGLE SOLDIER.
THE "TRENCH BROOM"
WAS DESIGNED
TO SWEEP THE ENEMY
OUT OF FOXHOLES.
BUT THE GUN WASN'T READY
UNTIL AFTER THE WAR ENDED,
SO THE GENERAL TRIED SELLING IT
TO THE AMERICAN PUBLIC.
ONE NOTORIOUS AD FEATURED
A COWBOY DEFENDING HIS RANCH
FROM BANDITS.
DEEMED SIMPLE, SAFE, STURDY,
AND SURE IN ACTION,
AN ORIGINAL TOMMY COULD FIRE
1,500 ROUNDS PER MINUTE.
GANGSTERS SAW THE POTENTIAL.
THE GUN WAS SUCH A FAVORITE
OF THE CHICAGO MOB
THAT IT WAS ALSO KNOWN
AS THE CHICAGO TYPEWRITER,
THE CHICAGO PIANO,
AND THE CHICAGO ORGAN GRINDER.
FOR CONCEALMENT, THE COMPACT GUN
COULD BE TOTED AROUND
IN A REFITTED
MUSICAL INSTRUMENT CASE.
THE THOMPSON DID MAKE IT
TO THE BATTLEFIELD
IN WORLD WAR II.
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS
WERE ORDERED
AT A COST OF NEARLY
$130 MILLION TOTAL.
BY THE END OF THE WAR,
LIGHTER AND CHEAPER COMPETITORS
ENDED THE TOMMY'S REIGN.
Tukufu:
OUR NEXT STORY INVESTIGATES
A DEATH THREAT SENT
TO ONE OF THE FIRST PRESIDENTS
OF THE UNITED STATES.
ON APRIL 14, 1865,
A MAN STANDING
IN THE SHADOWS
OF PRESIDENT ABRAHAM LINCOLN'S
THEATER BOX
FIRED ONE FINAL SHOT.
IT WAS THE FIRST ASSASSINATION
OF AN AMERICAN PRESIDENT,
AND JOHN WILKES BOOTH'S MOTIVES
HAVE BEEN QUESTIONED
AND STUDIED FOR GENERATIONS.
NOW, ALMOST 150 YEARS LATER,
MARSHA MULLIN
OF NASHVILLE, TENNESSEE,
HAS LEARNED OF A LETTER
SUPPOSEDLY WRITTEN
BY JOHN WILKES BOOTH'S FATHER
TO ANOTHER AMERICAN PRESIDENT.
TODAY SOMEBODY WOULD BE TAKEN
OFF TO JAIL IN FIVE MINUTES
FOR WRITING A LETTER
LIKE THAT.
MARSHA HAS INVITED ME
TO THE HERMITAGE,
PRESIDENT ANDREW JACKSON'S
FAMILY HOME IN NASHVILLE,
WHERE SHE IS CHIEF CURATOR.
SO WHAT DO YOU HAVE FOR ME?
WELL, A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO,
A VISITOR BROUGHT TO
OUR ATTENTION THIS LETTER,
WHICH WAS A DEATH THREAT
TO ANDREW JACKSON
WRITTEN IN 1835.
I REALLY DIDN'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT IT,
SO I GOT A COPY OF IT
FROM THE LIBRARY OF CONGRESS.
THE SIGNATURE ON
THE DEATH THREAT READS
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH.
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
WAS A VERY FAMOUS ACTOR,
BUT INTERESTINGLY ENOUGH,
HE WAS ALSO THE FATHER
OF JOHN WILKES BOOTH.
NOW, THAT'S AN INTERESTING
CONNECTION.
IT'S VERY INTERESTING.
IT'S DATED
THE 4th OF JULY, 1835,
FROM BROWER'S HOTEL,
PHILADELPHIA.
"YOU DAMNED OLD SCOUNDREL,
I WILL CUT YOUR THROAT
WHILST YOU ARE SLEEPING."
HE'S INSISTING THAT JACKSON
PARDON TWO MEN ON DEATH ROW.
"I'LL HAVE YOU BURNT
AT THE STAKE
"IN THE CITY OF WASHINGTON.
YOUR MASTER,
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH."
MAN, NOW THIS IS A THREAT.
SO THE FATHER OF THE GUY
WHO KILLED LINCOLN
THREATENED TO ASSASSINATE
A PRESIDENT.
WELL, THAT'S THE QUESTION.
BECAUSE WHEN YOU LOOK
AT THE BACK OF THE LETTER,
SOMEONE HAS WRITTEN
"ANONYMOUS."
AND SO THAT WAS VERY CURIOUS.
IS IT BY JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
OR NOT?
JACKSON SCHOLARS
SEEM TO BELIEVE
THAT IT WAS WRITTEN
BY SOMEONE ELSE.
WE'D LIKE TO KNOW
IF JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
REALLY WROTE THIS LETTER,
AND IF HE DID, WHY?
WELL, LET ME SEE IF I CAN FIND
AN ANSWER TO YOUR QUESTION.
THE SINS OF A FATHER
ARE NOT NECESSARILY VISITED
UPON THE SON.
BUT PRESIDENT LINCOLN'S MURDER
ALTERED AMERICAN HISTORY.
IF JOHN WILKES BOOTH'S FATHER
ALSO THREATENED THE LIFE
OF A SITTING PRESIDENT,
THAT'S CERTAINLY INTERESTING
AND POSSIBLY SIGNIFICANT.
JACKSON WAS THE 7th PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES
AND FIRST TOOK OFFICE
IN 1829.
JUNIUS BOOTH WAS THE POPULAR
SHAKESPEAREAN ACTOR OF THE DAY.
THE QUESTION IS,
WHY HAVE HISTORIANS DOUBTED
THAT JUNIUS BOOTH WROTE THIS
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
MARSHA'S LEFT ME
20th-CENTURY PUBLICATIONS
OF A JACKSON BIOGRAPHY
AND A COLLECTION
OF HIS CORRESPONDENCE.
BOTH VOLUMES INCLUDE MENTION
OF OUR LETTER.
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH HERE
IS IN QUOTATION MARKS.
BOOTH, IN QUOTATION MARKS,
TO ANDREW JACKSON,
JULY 4, 1835.
THE QUOTATION MARKS INDICATE
THE AUTHORS AND EDITORS
ALSO DOUBTED THAT BOOTH WROTE
THE DEATH THREAT.
I NEED TO FOUND OUT
IF THESE DOUBTS
ARE BASED ON
SOME ACTUAL EVIDENCE.
THE LETTER WRITER,
WHOEVER HE WAS,
WANTED TWO MEN PARDONED:
DE RUIZ AND DE SOTO.
I WONDER WHAT OTHER CLUES
THERE MIGHT BE.
IT SAYS DOWN HERE
IN A POSTSCRIPT,
"YOU KNOW ME, LOOK OUT."
DOES IT MEAN THAT
HE KNEW HIM PERSONALLY?
DOES IT MEAN
THAT HE KNEW OF HIM?
"I WROTE TO YOU
REPEATED CAUTIONS."
DID HE WRITE MORE THREATS
TO THE PRESIDENT?
THE PAPERS OF ANDREW JACKSON
PROJECT
AT THE UNIVERSITY OF TENNESSEE
IN KNOXVILLE
IS IN THE PROCESS OF PUBLISHING
AN UPDATED VERSION
OF EVERY KNOWN DOCUMENT
THAT JACKSON WROTE OR RECEIVED.
DAN FELLER IS THE DIRECTOR
AND EDITOR OF THE PROJECT.
LET'S GO INTO
THE JACKSON PAPERS.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
THIS LETTER BEFORE?
OH, YES, WE KNOW IT WELL.
WE DON'T THINK THAT THE REAL
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH WROTE IT.
OUR ASSUMPTION IS THAT THE
ORIGINAL NOTATION WAS CORRECT,
THAT IT'S ANONYMOUS.
DAN EXPLAINS THAT
PRESIDENT JACKSON'S STRONG-HAND
AND OFTEN UNPOPULAR POLICIES
HAD MADE HIM A LIGHTNING ROD
FOR CRITICISM AND THREATS.
SIX MONTHS BEFORE
OUR LETTER WAS WRITTEN,
HE WAS THE VICTIM OF
THE FIRST ASSASSINATION ATTEMPT
AGAINST AN AMERICAN PRESIDENT.
A DERANGED HOUSE PAINTER
ATTEMPTED TO SHOOT HIM
OUTSIDE THE CAPITOL BUILDING,
BUT THE PISTOL MISFIRED.
SHORTLY AFTER THAT,
THE WASHINGTON GLOBE PUBLISHED
SEVERAL COLUMNS
OF ASSASSINATION LETTERS
THAT IT SAID JACKSON
HAD RECEIVED.
LET ME PUT THESE UP
ON OUR COMPUTER SCREEN
SO YOU CAN READ THEM BETTER.
HERE'S ONE.
"DAMN YOUR OLD SOUL,
"IF YOU DO NOT DO SOMETHING
FOR THE GOOD OF THE COUNTRY,
I WILL MURDER YOU."
WOW.
DAN SAYS JACKSON
DREW PUBLIC CRITICISM
BECAUSE HE WANTED TO DO AWAY
WITH THE FEDERALLY CHARTERED
BANK OF THE UNITED STATES,
WHICH HE REGARDED AS AN
UNCONSTITUTIONAL CONCENTRATION
OF FINANCIAL POWER.
HERE'S ANOTHER ONE:
"REMOVE THEM DEPOSITS BACK AGAIN
AND RECHARTER THE BANK,
"OR YOU WILL CERTAINLY BE SHOT
IN LESS THAN TWO WEEKS,
AND THAT BY MYSELF!"
THE UNITED STATES SENATE
ACTUALLY CENSURED JACKSON
FOR REMOVING THE DEPOSITS,
THE ONLY TIME A PRESIDENT
HAS EVER BEEN CENSURED
BY THE SENATE.
DAN SAYS T RUIZ AND DE SOTO
MENTIONED IN OUR LETTER
WERE SPANISH PIRATES OPERATING
OUT OF HAVANA.
WITH TEN OTHERS,
THEY HAD ROBBED
AN AMERICAN MERCHANT SHIP
IN SEPTEMBER 1832.
THE PIRATES' CAPTURE
AND SUBSEQUENT TRIAL
ELECTRIFIED THE NATION.
THIS WAS A HUGE CASE.
IT HAD ALL OF THE ASPECTS
OF A MODERN SHOW TRIAL.
ONE OF THE SPANIARDS,
DE SOTO,
WAS PARDONED MOST LIKELY
BECAUSE HE PREVIOUSLY HAD SAVED
THE LIVES OF SOME
AMERICAN SAILORS.
DAN SAYS THE PARDON
WAS ALMOST CERTAINLY NOT
AS A RESULT
OF THE DEATH THREAT.
HOW SERIOUSLY WAS
THIS THREAT TAKEN?
DAN DOUBTS THERE WAS
ANY OFFICIAL INVESTIGATION
INTO THE LETTER.
THE OFFICE OF THE PRESIDENT
DID NOT HAVE
THE PROTECTIVE LAYERS
IT HAS TODAY.
THERE WAS NO SECRET SERVICE,
THERE WAS NO FEDERAL BUREAU
OF INVESTIGATION,
THERE WERE REALLY
NO WHITE HOUSE POLICE.
IN FACT, ASSASSINATING
THE PRESIDENT
OR THREATENING TO DO SO
WAS NOT A FEDERAL CRIME.
HERE HE SAYS, "I WROTE TO YOU
REPEATED CAUTIONS."
DO YOU KNOW OF ANY
OTHER COMMUNICATIONS
BETWEEN BOOTH AND JACKSON?
IF THERE WERE ANY,
WE WOULD HAVE SEEN THEM.
WE KNOW OF ONE LETTER
FROM SOMEONE CALLING HIMSELF
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH TO JACKSON,
AND THIS IS IT.
AND THAT'S IT.
AND NOT ONLY NO LETTERS
FROM BOOTH OR TO BOOTH,
BUT NO MENTION OF BOOTH
IN JACKSON'S CORRESPONDENCE.
WHOEVER WANTED
THESE PIRATES PARDONED,
DAN'S CONVINCED
IT WASN'T BOOTH.
EVERY HISTORIAN
PREVIOUS TO US,
EVERY JACKSON BIOGRAPHER,
HAS ASSUMED THAT BOOTH
DIDN'T WRITE IT.
SOMEONE IN HIS OFFICE --
AND HE HAD A NUMBER OF CLERKS
WORKING FOR HIM --
PROBABLY WROTE THIS WORD
"ANONYMOUS."
JACKSON DID NOT WRITE IT.
IT DOESN'T APPEAR TO BE
JACKSON'S HANDWRITING, NO.
HAS THERE BEEN AN ANALYSIS
OF THE HANDWRITING
IN THIS LETTER?
AS FAR AS I KNOW, NO ONE HAS
EVER TAKEN IT TO THAT STEP
BECAUSE THEY THOUGHT
IT WAS UNNECESSARY.
THAT SEEMS A CURIOUS OMISSION.
THE FOLGER SHAKESPEARE LIBRARY
IN WASHINGTON, D.C.,
HAS SEVERAL JUNIUS BOOTH
LETTERS IN THEIR COLLECTION.
HEATHER WOLFE IS CURATOR
OF MANUSCRIPTS.
SHE'S MADE SPECIAL ARRANGEMENTS
WITH THE LIBRARY OF CONGRESS
TO OBTAIN THE ORIGINAL THREAT
TO JACKSON.
HEATHER, NICE TO MEET YOU.
SO THIS IS THE ORIGINAL LETTER.
I PICKED TWO OF OUR
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH LETTERS
FOR A HANDWRITING ANALYSIS.
I PICKED THESE TWO LETTERS
BECAUSE THEY WERE CLOSEST
IN DATE AND FORMAT
TO THE 1835 LETTER
TO GENERAL JACKSON.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME
HEATHER HAS SEEN
THE ORIGINAL LETTER
TO JACKSON,
AND A COUPLE OF ITEMS
STRIKE HER AS ODD.
HE SIGNS THE LETTER TO JACKSON
WITH HIS FULL NAME,
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH.
ALL OF THE LETTERS AT THE FOLGER
ARE SIGNED J.B. BOOTH,
AND THAT WAS HIS TYPICAL
SIGNATURE.
THE REST OF THE LETTER
LOOKS AS IF
IT COULD'VE FLOWED
FROM THE SAME PEN.
AND YOU SEE HERE, "I WROTE
TO YOU REPEATED CAUTIONS,"
AND SEE THE BOTTOM OF THAT C,
HOW IT LOOPS AROUND
DRAMATICALLY?
WELL, IN THIS LETTER HERE,
WE SEE THE WORD "CAMP"
WITH THAT SAME VERY DISTINCTIVE
MAJUSCULE C,
WHICH IS VERY UNIQUE
TO JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH.
ONE OF THE MOST DISTINCTIVE
ATTRIBUTES HE HAS
IS THE CROSSBAR
ON THE MINISCULE T's.
SO IF YOU LOOK AT THE WORD "THE"
IN THIS LETTER,
THE CROSSBAR GOES FULLY ACROSS
NOT JUST THE T
BUT ALSO THE H AND THE E.
IF BOOTH DIDN'T WRITE THIS
HIMSELF,
SHE SAYS THE FORGER WAS
AT THE TOP OF HIS CLASS.
HEATHER'S MADE
ANOTHER DISCOVERY.
THIS LETTER FROM 1834
MENTIONS THAT HE NEEDED
TO ESCAPE THE FARM
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS
AND GO TO PHILADELPHIA,
AND IT SAYS, "THEREFORE
I STROLLED TO PHILADELPHIA.
BROWER'S HOTEL IS NOW
ABOUT THE BEST IN THAT CITY."
SO HE HAS A HISTORY
OF FREQUENTING
THE BROWER'S HOTEL
IN PHILADELPHIA.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DID JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
WRITE THIS LETTER?
BASED ON HANDWRITING ANALYSIS
ALONE,
YES, IT IS A JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
LETTER.
BUT I'M NOT A BOOTH EXPERT,
SO I THINK THAT'S A QUESTION
FOR BOOTH SCHOLARS.
WE'D NEED TO FIND OUT MORE
ABOUT THE CONTEXT OF THE LETTER.
WHY DID A FAMOUS
SHAKESPEAREAN ACTOR
CARE ENOUGH ABOUT THE FATE
OF TWO SPANISH PIRATES
TO HAVE PENNED
A DEATH THREAT
TO THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES?
GENE SMITH HAS AGREED
TO MEET ME
AT THE FOLGER LIBRARY'S
ELIZABETHAN THEATER.
HE'S THE AUTHOR OF A BOOK
ON THE BOOTH FAMILY'S INFLUENCE
ON AMERICAN THEATER.
IN ADDITION TO BEING
A GREAT ACTOR,
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH WAS
A GREAT MADMAN ALL HIS LIFE.
THERE'S NO QUESTION
HE WAS INSANE.
GENE SAYS THAT THE WILD
AND ERRATIC BEHAVIOR ONSTAGE
LED BOOTH TO BE DUBBED
"THE MAD TRAGEDIAN."
HIS BOUTS OF LUNACY
COULD INTERRUPT A PRODUCTION.
HE WOULD RUN AWAY
FROM THE THEATER
AND BE FOUND WALKING NAKED
DOWN THE STREET.
BOOTH'S EXCESSIVE DRINKING
EXACERBATED HIS MADNESS.
THEATER MANAGERS
WOULD LOCK HIM UP
TO KEEP HIM
FROM GETTING DRUNK.
FREQUENTLY, HE WOULD ESCAPE
AND SIMPLY VANISH
FOR THREE OR FOUR DAYS.
DID HIS FITS OF MADNESS
LEAD HIM TO ACTS OF VIOLENCE?
YES, BUT ONLY
VERY OCCASIONALLY.
HE WAS CAPABLE IN
THE MIDDLE OF A PERFORMANCE
OF BECOMING SO INVOLVED
IN KILLING DESDEMONA AS OTHELLO
THAT WHEN THE MOMENT CAME
TO PRESS THE PILLOW
AGAINST DESDEMONA'S FACE,
PEOPLE WERE AFRAID HE WOULD
ACTUALLY MURDER THE ACTRESS.
WELL, THIS LETTER
IS A THREAT
TO ASSASSINATE
PRESIDENT ANDREW JACKSON.
COULD THAT VIOLENT BEHAVIOR
HAVE EXTENDED TO MURDER?
IT IS POSSIBLE.
HOWEVER, IT'S IMPORTANT
TO KNOW
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
HAD A REVERENCE FOR LIFE
THAT WAS EXTRAORDINARY.
GENERALLY, HE HURT NOBODY
BUT HIMSELF:
HIS KIDS WERE FORBIDDEN
TO SWAT A FLY,
HE WOULD NOT CUT DOWN
A TREE.
HIS DEATH THREAT,
IF BOOTH PENNED IT,
MAY HAVE BEEN A BOUT
OF ALCOHOLIC MADNESS,
HIS REVERENCE FOR LIFE
BIZARRELY PROVOKING HIM
TO THREATEN MURDER.
MY GUESS WOULD BE
THAT MR. BOOTH PROBABLY READ
THAT JACKSON WAS CONSIDERING
THE EXECUTION OF THESE TWO MEN
AND, IN ONE OF HIS FRENZIES,
THREATENED TO KILL HIM.
HE DOUBTS PRESIDENT JACKSON
TOOK IT SERIOUSLY.
INDEED, THE LETTER SAYS,
"YOU KNOW ME,"
AND HE DID KNOW HIM.
JACKSON AND BOOTH
WERE CLOSE PERSONAL FRIENDS.
I THINK JACKSON WOULD'VE
PROBABLY SAID,
"WELL, THAT'S BOOTH FOR YOU,"
AND JACKSON WOULD'VE
LAUGHED IT OFF.
GENE PAINTS A PICTURE
OF A TURBULENT
AND DEEPLY TROUBLED MAN
FREQUENTLY ABSENT
FROM HIS FAMILY.
JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH
WAS AWAY ON THE ROAD,
TROUPING AROUND AS AN ACTOR
FOR MUCH OF THE YEAR.
BUT GENE IS RELUCTANT
TO MAKE ANY CONNECTION
BETWEEN THE DEATH THREAT
JUNIUS BOOTH MAY HAVE MADE
TO PRESIDENT JACKSON
AND HIS SON'S MURDER OF
ABRAHAM LINCOLN 30 YEARS LATER.
I THINK IT'S
EXCEEDINGLY IMPROBABLE.
HIS KILLING OF ABRAHAM LINCOLN
WAS SO ALIEN
TO HIS FATHER'S REVERENCE
FOR LIFE
THAT THERE CANNOBE
ANY TRACEABLE PATH.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT TO MAKE
OF ALL OF THIS,
AND I STILL DON'T HAVE
ANY SOLID EVIDENCE
TO SUPPORT
THE HANDWRITING ANALYSIS.
[ cell phone rings ]
HEY, DAN, HOW YOU DOING?
IT'S DAN FELLER.
SEEMS OUR MEETING
PROMPTED HIM
TO DO SOME ADDITIONAL RESEARCH.
I TELL DAN ABOUT
THE HANDWRITING COMPARISON
AND WHAT ELSE I'VE LEARNED
ABOUT JUNIUS BOOTH.
IT'S BEEN SUGGESTED TO ME
THAT JACKSON AND BOOTH
WERE ACTUALLY FRIENDS
AND THAT THIS LETTER
WAS WRITTEN IN JEST.
I DOUBT THAT VERY MUCH.
WE HAVE HERE ALL
OF ANDREW JACKSON'S LETTERS
THAT ANYONE KNOWS ABOUT;
WE KNOW OF NO EVIDENCE
TO PUT JACKSON AND BOOTH
TOGETHER IN ANY WAY.
HIS TEAM HAS UNCOVERED SEVERAL
NEW PIECES OF INFORMATION.
OUR LETTER'S DATED JULY 4th.
HE'S BEEN ABLE TO FIGURE OUT
BOOTH'S WHEREABOUTS THAT DAY.
THESE ARE NEWSPAPER
ADVERTISEMENTS
SHOWING THAT BOOTH WAS
INDEED IN PHILADELPHIA
ON JULY 3rd AND 4th.
HE WAS SCHEDULED TO PLAY
OTHELLO ON THE 3rd
AT THE CHESTNUT STREET
THEATRE...
I SEE.
AND SCHEDULED TO PLAY
RICHARD III ON THE 4th.
THAT PUTS BOOTH
IN PHILADELPHIA
AT THE TIME THE LETTER
WAS WRITTEN.
AND HERE'S
THE REAL CLINCHER.
THIS IS ANOTHER LETTER THAT
BOOTH WROTE IN AUGUST OF 1835.
HE APOLOGIZES FOR "THE
UNGRATEFUL AND SHAMEFUL CONDUCT
"I HAVE EVINCED TOWARD
THE WORTHY MANAGERS
"OF THE CHESTNUT STREET THEATRE
ON A RECENT OCCASION,
FRIDAY, JULY 3rd,
AND SATURDAY THE 4th.
IN FACT, HE DID NOT PLAY
ON JULY 3rd AND 4th;
HE DIDN'T SHOW UP.
SO HE WAS THERE, AND MAYBE
IN ONE OF HIS FITS OF MADNESS,
DID NOT PERFORM.
EXACTLY.
BUT AS FOR THREATENING
TO ASSASSINATE THE PRESIDENT,
I STILL DON'T HAVE
A SMOKING GUN.
BUT LOOK FURTHER DOWN
IN THE LETTER.
THERE AT THE END,
JUNIUS BOOTH HIMSELF GIVES ME
MY FINAL PIECE
OF THE PUZZLE.
"MY INSANE BEHAVIOR..."
I THINK I FINALLY HAVE
AN ANSWER FOR MARSHA.
VERY INTERESTING
INVESTIGATION.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR THE OPPORTUNITY
TO GET INTO THE LIFE
OF JUNIUS BRUTUS BOOTH.
I TELL MARSHA
THAT THE HANDWRITING
OF THIS ASSASSINATION THREAT
MATCHED OTHER LETTERS
PENNED BY BOOTH.
THAT'S COOL;
I AM REALLY PLEASED.
BUT WHAT TIED
THE CIRCUMSTANTIAL EVIDENCE
TOGETHER WAS AN OPEN LETTER
FROM BOOTH
THAT SEEMED TO BE
AN ADMISSION OF GUILT.
HE SAYS, "MY INSANE BEHAVIOR
IN WRITING INSOLENT LETTERS
"TO MY BEST PATRONS AND TO
THE AUTHORITIES OF THIS COUNTRY
I CAN SCARCELY HOPE
WILL BE PARDONED."
"THE AUTHORITIES
OF THIS COUNTRY."
YOU THINK HE'S REFERRING TO
PRESIDENT ANDREW JACKSON HERE?
I'LL BET HE IS, BECAUSE
ONE SENTENCE FURTHER DOWN,
HE SAYS, "MAY GOD PRESERVE
GENERAL JACKSON
AND THIS HAPPY REPUBLIC."
DAN SAYS
OUR HANDWRITING ANALYSIS
AND HIS QUESTIONING
OF CONVENTIONAL WISDOM
HAVE CORRECTED
THE HISTORICAL RECORD.
PRESIDENT LINCOLN'S KILLER,
JOHN WILKES BOOTH,
WAS FATHERED BY A MAN
WHO ALSO THREATENED
TO MURDER A SITTING PRESIDENT.
WE HAD ASSUMED, AS THOSE
BEFORE US HAD ASSUMED,
THAT THE REAL BOOTH
DIDN'T WRITE THIS LETTER
ON THE BASIS OF THAT
ONE WORD, "ANONYMOUS."
IT TURNED OUT HE DID.
IT REMINDS US ALWAYS
TO CHECK OUR FACTS,
ALWAYS TO GO BACK
AND VERIFY,
EVEN WHEN WE THINK WE KNOW
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED.
THAT IS AMAZING.
I'M SHOCKED.
I MEAN, IT'S AN INTERESTING
COINCIDENCE
THAT HE WROTE SUCH A LETTER
AND THAT HIS SON ENDED UP
ASSASSINATING LINCOLN.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR THE OPPORTUNITY
TO INVESTIGATE THIS STORY.
THANK YOU.
WHOSE JOB IS IT
TO PROTECT THE PRESIDENT?
WELL, BEFORE
THE SECRET SERVICE,
IT WAS SOMETIMES THE ARMY,
SOMETIMES THE LOCAL POLICE.
BUT LOTS OF TIMES,
IT WAS NO ONE.
JEFFERSON WALKED TO
HIS OWN INAUGURATION UNGUARDED.
MARTIN VAN BUREN WALKED
TO CHURCH ON SUNDAYS ALONE.
ON THE NIGHT LINCOLN
WAS ASSASSINATED,
A LOCAL WASHINGTON PATROLMAN
HAD BEEN ASSIGNED
TO PROTECT THE PRESIDENT,
BUT HE ABANDONED HIS POST TO
GET A BETTER VIEW OF THE PLAY.
THE SECRET SERVICE
WAS CREATED
FOUR MONTHS AFTER
LINCOLN'S ASSASSINATION
NOT TO PROTECT THE PRESIDENT
BUT TO PROTECT THE ECONOMY.
ITS AGENTS WERE CHARGED
WITH FIGHTING COUNTERFEITING.
TWO MORE PRESIDENTS
WOULD BE ASSASSINATED
BEFORE PRESIDENTIAL PROTECTION
BECAME A FULL-TIME
NATIONAL PRIORITY.
ONE GUNMAN KILLED
PRESIDENT GARFIELD
AT A WASHINGTON TRAIN STATION
IN 1881
AND ANOTHER GUNMAN SHOT
PRESIDENT McKINLEY
AT THE PAN-AM EXPO IN BUFFALO
IN 1901.
AFTER THREE ASSASSINATIONS
IN LESS THAN 40 YEARS,
CONGRESS FINALLY ASSIGNED
THE SECRET SERVICE
THE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THE SAFETY OF THE PRESIDENT
AT ALL TIMES.
Wes:
OUR LAST STORY EXPLORES
A BLACK MARKET TRADE
THAT SCANDALIZED
POST-CIVIL-WAR OHIO.
SINCE BEFORE THE TIME
OF THE PHARAOHS,
CIVILIZATIONS HAVE BEEN
BURYING THEIR DEAD
ALONG WITH PERSONAL EFFECTS,
JEWELRY AND ARTIFACTS
THAT COULD
MAKE A THIEF RICH
OVERNIGHT.
BUT LEFT UNGUARDED,
THESE COFFINS AND TOMBS
FREQUENTLY BECAME THE TREASURE
CHESTS OF GRAVE ROBBERS.
OVER THE CENTURIES,
COUNTLESS SITES
HAVE BEEN DESECRATED,
LOOTED,
AND VALUABLE HISTORIC ARTIFACTS
LOST TO THE BLACK MARKET.
HENRY DORRUM
OF CHESANING, MICHIGAN,
BELIEVES HE'S FOUND
THE 19th-CENTURY ANSWER
TO THIS HISTORIC PROBLEM.
I'VE BEEN COLLECTING
FOR ABOUT 25 YEARS,
AND THIS IS THE MOST UNUSUAL
OBJECT I'VE EVER FOUND.
[ ♪♪♪ ]
I WANT TO GET A LOOK
AT WHAT KIND OF STRANGE GADGET
HENRY BOUGHT FOR HIMSELF.
WELL, WHAT'S IN THE BOX?
I DON'T KNOW.
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
AN EXPLOSIVE DEVICE.
IT'S A HEAVY LITTLE DEVIL.
OH, THAT IS HEAVY.
WHERE'D YOU GET THIS THING?
AT A FARM AUCTION
IN SAGINAW COUNTY, MICHIGAN.
I LIKE UNUSUAL ITEMS
OF ALL KINDS.
I'M A COLLECTOR OF ANYTHING.
I'VE GOT TO ASK YOU,
ARE YOU SURE
THAT IT'S NOT GOING
TO EXPLODE?
OH, NO, IT'S BEEN
THOROUGHLY CHECKED.
I'VE HAD IT
FOR A LONG TIME,
AND YOU CAN LOOK DOWN
IN THERE,
AND IT'S COMPLETELY VOID
OF ANY POWDER.
HENRY EXPLAINS THAT ONCE
WHEN HE HAD IT ON DISPLAY
AT A BALTIMORE GUN SHOW,
A PASSERBY CLAIMED
HE RECOGNIZED THE DEVICE.
HE TOLD HENRY IT WAS
A KIND OF GRAVE ALARM.
I'D SEEN A PICTURE OF IT
IN A MAGAZINE YEARS AGO,
AND THAT'S WHAT IT WAS,
A GRAVE ALARM.
I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU, I'VE
NEVER HEARD OF SUCH A THING.
THE STRANGER TOLD HIM
GRAVE ALARMS WERE USED
TO PROTECT JEWELRY
AND OTHER VALUABLES
THAT MAY HAVE BEEN BURIED
WITH THE DECEASED.
THEY WOULD PUT ONE OF THESE
IN THE CASKET,
AND WHEN THE GRAVE ROBBER
OPENS THE COFFIN,
IT'S GOING TO BLOW UP
IN HIS FACE.
WHAT IS IT THAT YOU WANT ME
TO FIND OUT ABOUT THIS?
I WANT YOU GUYS TO FIND OUT
IF THIS TRULY IS A GRAVE ALARM.
WELL, HENRY, I'LL SEE
WHAT I CAN DIG UP.
I CAN'T FIND ANY MAKER'S MARK
OR SERIAL NUMBER,
WHICH IS A LITTLE ODD IF THIS
HAD BEEN MANUFACTURED FOR SALE.
I'M SKEPTICAL THIS IS AN ALARM,
AS HENRY BELIEVES.
IT LOOKS MORE LIKE SOME
KIND OF CIVIL-WAR-ERA WEAPON.
THIS IS A BOMB.
I MEAN, THIS THING WOULD'VE HELD
MAYBE HALF A POUND,
THREE-QUARTERS OF A POUND
OF BLACK POWDER IN HERE.
IT WEIGHS ABOUT EIGHT POUNDS
AND IT'S MADE OF CAST IRON,
WHICH WOULD'VE TURNED INTO
SHARDS OF DEADLY SHRAPNEL
IF THIS THING
HAD EVER EXPLODED.
THIS IS A SPRING-LOADED HAMMER
THAT WOULD'VE BEEN SET
BY MOVING THIS METAL BAR
ON THE COLLAR AROUND.
IF SOMEBODY STEPPED ON IT,
THIS FIRING MECHANISM
WOULD'VE ALMOST CERTAINLY
HAVE BEEN ACTIVATED.
SO WHEN THIS LITTLE COLLAR
IS MOVED
EVEN A FRACTION OF AN INCH,
THE HAMMER DROPS, AND THEN
IT HITS AN EXPLOSIVE CAP,
ALMOST LIKE A CAP GUN.
AND IF YOU LOOK, YOU'LL SEE THAT
THERE'S A HOLE ON THAT NIPPLE,
SO A SPARK WOULD TRAVEL
INTO THAT INTERIOR,
IGNITE THE GUNPOWDER,
AND BAM!
I'VE COME OUT
TO THE CORDOVA DRAGWAY PARK,
ABOUT TWO HOURS WEST
OF CHICAGO,
TO SEE JUST HOW DANGEROUS OUR
EXPLOSIVE DEVICE WOULD'VE BEEN.
LARRY LEFFERTS
OF CENTRAL STATES FIREWORKS
CONFIRMED THE AMOUNT
OF BLACK POWDER
OUR DEVICE WOULD'VE CARRIED.
WHAT WE DID WAS WE TOOK
THREE-QUARTERS OF A POUND
OF BLACK POWDER
AND WE BURIED THEM
AND PUT A LITTLE BIT
OF DIRT ON TOP
TO SIMULATE WHAT
IT MAY LOOK LIKE.
FIRE IN THE HOLE!
Wes:
WHOA, THAT THING COULD DO
SOME SERIOUS DAMAGE!
ABOUT AN HOUR FROM THE DRAGWAY
IS T ROCK ISLAND ARSENAL.
ESTABLISHED IN 1862,
IT'S THE NATION'S LARGEST
GOVERNMENT-OWNED
AND OPERATED ARSENAL.
KRIS LEINICKE IS
THE CURATOR OF THE MUSEUM,
WHICH HOUSES
AN EXTENSIVE COLLECTION
OF HISTORIC MILITARY WEAPONS.
THIS IS THE DEVICE
I WANTED TO SHOW YOU.
OKAY.
WOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
IT COULD BE?
IT LOOKS TO ME LIKE IT MIGHT
BE A CIVIL-WAR TORPEDO.
TORPEDO?
KRIS EXPLAINS THAT TODAY,
TORPEDO IS KNOWN
AS AN UNDERWATER WEAPON
LAUNCHED FROM A SUBMARINE
OR WARSHIP,
BUT IT ONCE HAD
A MUCH BROADER DEFINITION.
BEFORE THE FIRST WORLD WAR,
A TORPEDO MEANT ANY HIDDEN
EXPLOSIVE OR LAND MINE.
KRIS SAYS THAT PERCUSSION CAPS,
WHICH FIT OVER THE NIPPLES
AND PRODUCE THE SPARKS
THAT IGNITED THE GUNPOWDER,
WERE A CIVIL-WAR TECHNOLOGY.
SO IS THIS
A MILITARY DEVICE, THEN?
I DON'T THINK IT IS,
BECAUSE IT'S NOT MARKED,
AND A LOT OF MILITARY
EQUIPMENT AT THAT TIME
DID HAVE MARKINGS.
THE OTHER THING IS THAT
THE COLLAR ON THE NIPPLE
IS DIFFERENT THAN ON MILITARY
WEAPONS OF THAT TIME PERIOD.
LET ME SHOW YOU.
WE HAVE HERE
A CIVIL-WAR WEAPON
THAT WAS MADE
AT WATERTOWN ARSENAL,
AND YOU CAN SEE
THAT THIS ITEM THAT WE HAVE
HAS A SQRE COLLAR.
IT'S A TINY DETAIL, BUT KRIS
EXPLAINS THAT THE U.S. MILITARY
ROUTINELY USED SQUARE COLLARS
ON PERCUSSION WEAPONS.
OUR COLLAR IS RECTANGULAR.
I ASK KRIS IF SHE THINKS
THERE'S ANYTHING
TO WARREN'S IDEA
THAT THE DEVICE WAS DESIGNED
TO DETER GRAVE ROBBERS.
THAT'S REALLY INTERESTING, BUT
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF THAT BEFORE.
AND IF THIS HAD BEEN BURIED,
KRIS SPOTS WHAT APPEARS TO BE
A FATAL FLAW
IN THE DESIGN
OF OUR TORPEDO.
THE OTHER PROBLEM IS,
ONCE YOU BURIED IT,
YOU'D HAVE DIRT IN HERE,
AND THEN HOW WOULD THE HAMMER
HIT THE PERCUSSION CAP
THAT'S ON THE NIPPLE
TO CREATE THE EXPLOSION?
BUT IT'S DEFINITELY
PROFESSIONALLY MADE,
SO IT HAS TO HAVE SOME KIND
OF PRACTICAL USE.
YOU KNOW, IF OUR DEVICE
REALLY WAS MEANT
TO DETER GRAVE ROBBERS,
THERE'S GOTO BE SOME ACCOUNT
OF ONE OF THESE GOING OFF.
I TRY SEARCHING ONLINE
TO SEE WHAT I CAN FIND
ABOUT GRAVE ALARMS.
I DON'T TURN ANYTHING UP
SEARCHING UNDER GRAVE ALARMS,
BUT GRAVE TORPEDO,
WHICH IS THE TERM KRIS USED,
RETURNS A CURIOUS HIT.
OKAY, HERE'S AN ARTICLE
FROM THE RICHWOOD GAZETTE,
1881 IN OHIO:
"GRAVE ROBBER KILLED."
"THREE MEN WHO ATTEMPTED
TO ROB A GRAVE
"NEAR GANN,
IN KNOX COUNTY, OHIO,
"MET WITH A HORRIBLE OBSTACLE.
WHEN NEARING THE COFFIN,
THEY STRUCK A TORPEDO."
SO THESE THINGS
REALLY DID EXIST.
ONE OF THESE DEVICES,
PATENTED IN 1881,
SOUNDS SIMILAR
TO OURS.
THOMAS HOWELL
OF CIRCLEVILLE, OHIO,
PATENTED
AN EXPLODING SHELL
THAT WAS BURIED
RIGHT ABOVE A COFFIN.
AND IF ROBBERS TRIED
TO DIG UP THE COFFIN,
"THE SHELL WOULD EXPLODE,
INJURING OR KILLING
THE THIEVES."
IT APPEARS THAT IN THESE CASES,
AT LEAST, THE GRAVE ROBBERS
WEREN'T TRYING TO SWIPE JEWELRY
AND OTHER VALUABLES,
THEY WERE TRYING
TO STEAL BODIES.
IT SAYS THAT DURING THE 1800s,
MEDICAL SCHOOLS STOLE CADAVERS
TO DEMONSTRATE GROSS ANATOMY
TO THE STUDENTS
AND THAT THIS WAS PARTICULARLY
A PROBLEM IN OHIO.
SCOTT GAMPHER IS THE DIRECTOR
OF HISTORY COLLECTIONS
AT THE CINCINNATI MUSEUM CENTER
AT UNION TERMINAL.
HE'S NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE OUR DEVICE,
BUT HE UNDERSTANDS THE HISTORIC
NEED TO PREVENT BODY SNATCHING.
THERE WERE A LOT
OF DISSECTIONS
THAT WERE TAKING PLACE
IN THESE MEDICAL COLLEGES,
AND THUS A NEED
FOR A LOT OF CADAVERS.
BETWEEN 1865 AND 1890,
THE NUMBER OF MEDICAL SCHOOLS
IN THE U.S. ALMOST DOUBLED.
CINCINNATI-AREA MEDICAL SCHOOLS
COMPETED WITH EACH OTHER
TO OFFER PRACTICAL EXPERIENCE
TO STUDENTS.
BUT BODIES WERE NOT
EASY TO COME BY:
THE CHURCH OBJECTED,
AND MANY STATES
ONLY PERMITTED THE BODIES
OF EXECUTED CRIMINALS
TO BE USED FOR DISSECTION.
AND SO, REALLY, THE ONLY AVENUE
FOR THESE SCHOOLS
TO OBTAIN CADAVERS
WAS THROUGH THE BLACK MARKET.
IN OTHER WORDS, BY DOING
BUSINESS WITH GRAVE ROBBERS.
IN THE 1870s, PUBLIC CONCERN
ABOUT BODY SNATCHING
WAS AT A FEVER PITCH
IN OHIO IN PARTICULAR
BECAUSE OF
A NOTORIOUS INCIDENT.
THE BODY OF
JOHN SCOTT HARRISON,
FATHER OF FUTURE PRESIDENT
BENJAMINM A ROPE
DOWN A DARK SHAFT
AT THE MEDICAL COLLEGE OF OHIO,
PROVOKING ENORMOUS OUTRAGE.
IT WAS PARTICULARLY BAD
BECAUSE MEASURES HAD BEEN TAKEN
BY THE HARRISON FAMILY
TO PREVENT THIS VERY THING
FROM HAPPENING.
SCOTT SHOWS ME
AN ARTICLE
FROM THE CINCINNATI
DAILY COMMERCIAL
WRITTEN IN 1878 JUST AFTER
HARRISON'S BODY WAS STOLEN.
"IF CEMENTED WALLS CAREFULLY
AND SKILLFULLY CONSTRUCTED,
"AND VAST WEIGHTS, REQUIRING THE
STRENGTH OF MANY MEN TO LIFT,
"AND HIRED AND PRE-PAID WATCHMEN
"COULD NOT SAVE THEIR LOVED
AND HONORED PARENT'S GRAVE
FROM DESECRATION AND DISHONOR,
WHAT COULD?"
WOW.
AND I THINK THAT'S
ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT SHOCKED THE PUBLIC
SO MUCH:
"WELL, IF IT COULD HAPPEN
TO THE HARRISONS,
IT COULD HAPPEN
TO ANYBODY."
THE PUBLIC HAD
RUN OUT OF WAYS
TO SECURE
THEIR LOVED ONE'S GRAVE,
SO THEY TURNED TO DEADLY
EXPLOSIVES AS A LAST RESORT.
BUT IS OUR DEVICE REALLY
ONE OF THESE TORPEDOES?
WITHOUT A MAKER'S MARK
OR A CLEAR EXPLANATION
FOR HOW IT MIGHT'VE WORKED,
I'M STILL NOT SURE
WHAT WE HAVE.
SCOTT PUT ME IN CONTACT
WITH PAUL MAYBERRY,
THE LOCAL HISTORIAN
OF PICKAWAY COUNTY, OHIO.
PICKAWAY INCLUDES
THE TOWN OF CIRCLEVILLE,
WHERE THOMAS HOWELL
INVENTED HIS TORPEDO.
MY RESEARCH LED ME
TO CIRCLEVILLE
BECAUSE OF THIS OBJECT.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS?
WELL, THAT'S REALLY SOMETHING.
PAUL HAS NEVER SEEN
ONE OF THESE BEFORE,
BUT HE SAYS GRAVE TORPEDOES
HAVE A LONG HISTORY
IN THE REGION.
OUR LOCAL CEMETERY
ABOLISHED THE USE OF THEM,
I THINK, IN 1890 BECAUSE IT WAS
TOO MUCH OF A DANGER
TO THE PEOPLE WHO WERE
WORKING IN THE CEMETERY.
SUPPOSEDLY THERE WAS A GUY
NAMED THOMAS HOWELL
WHO LIVED HERE IN CIRCLEVILLE
WHO MADE DEVICES LIKE THIS.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF HOWELL?
YES, I HAVE.
I'VE DONE SOME RESEARCH
ON THOMAS HOWELL.
HE WAS A WATCH MAKER AND TIMES
GOT A LITTLE TOUGH FOR HIM,
AND HE DECIDED TO RESOLVE
SOME OF THE PROBLEMS
WE HAD WITH GRAVE ROBBING.
PAUL ASSEMBLED A NUMBER
OF LOCAL ARTICLES ON HOWELL
THAT HE COPIED
FROM OLD NEWSPAPERS.
THIS IS SOME OF THE ADVERTISING
THAT HE DID.
SO IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S FROM THE NEWSPAPER
FROM JULY 11, 1879.
THE AD SAYS,
"SLEEP WELL, SWEET ANGEL.
"LET NO FEARS OF GHOULS
DISTURB THY REST,
"FOR ABOVE THY SHROUDED FORM
LIES A TORPEDO,
"READY TO MAKE MINCE-MEAT
OF ANYONE
WHO ATTEMPTS TO CONVEY YOU
TO THE PICKLING VAT."
WOW, THAT IS INCREDIBLE!
I MEAN, THAT'S PRETTY GOOD
DIRECT MARKETING, ISN'T IT?
IT IS.
BUT THE PICTURE OF HOWELL'S
GRAVE TORPEDO
LOOKS NOTHING LIKE OURS.
DO WE HAVE
A GRAVE TORPEDO?
AND HOW WOULD IT HAVE WORKED?
HERE'S THE PROBLEM
THAT I HAVE.
IF YOU SET THIS THING
AND YOU PUT IT INTO A GRAVE,
WHAT'S TO PREVENT IT FROM
EXPLODING IN YOUR FACE?
WELL, THIS IS
AN INGENIOUS DEVICE.
WHAT PAUL SHOWS ME NEXT
GIVES ME THE ANSWER I NEED
FOR WARREN.
WHEN YOU FIRST SHOWED ME
THIS THING
AND YOU THOUGHT IT WAS
SOME SORT OF A GRAVE ALARM,
I SAID, "COME ON,
THIS GUY'S CRAZY!
IT COULDN'T BE
A GRAVE ALARM."
BUT AS I GOT INTO
THE INVESTIGATION,
I DISCOVERED THAT
THIS IS NOT SO MUCH AN ALARM
AS IT IS A DEADLY WEAPON.
OH, YEAH?
I TELL HENRY
THAT HIS DEVICE WAS DESIGNED
TO DETER THIEVES STEALING
BODIES, NOT VALUABLES.
WELL, THE GUYS I TALKED TO
WERE HALF RIGHT, ANYWAY.
HERE'S THE THING
I COULDN'T FIGURE OUT:
HOW COULD YOU PUT THIS
INTO A GRAVE,
SET THE TRIGGERS,
AND FILL THE GRAVE UP
WITHOUT BLOWING
YOUR HEAD OFF?
YOU GOT ME IN SUSPENSE HERE!
THOMAS HOWELL WAS SO SUCCESSFUL
WITH HIS FIRST GRAVE TORPEDO
THAT HE DESIGNED
ANOTHER ONE,
AND I HAVE A PATENT
FOR THAT ONE HERE.
NO, REALLY?
"GRAVE TORPEDO,
DECEMBER 20, 1881."
THE OLD PATENT PAPERS
SHOW A CURIOUS PARABOLA,
OR ARC, OVER THE TOP
OF OUR TORPEDO,
AND SUDDENLY I UNDERSTAND HOW
OUR DEVICE IS SUPPOSED TO WORK.
WHAT'S MISSING FROM HERE
IS A THIN METAL SHIELD
THAT FIT OVER THIS
THAT HAD A HOLE
IN THE MIDDLE...
RIGHT.
THAT ACCORDING TO THE PATENT
PAPERS, YOU'D TAKE A LONG TUBE,
LIKE A STANDPIPE, YOU'D
PUT A FUNNEL UP AT THE TOP,
AFTER THIS IS BURIED
IN THE GRAVE...
CORRECT.
AND YOU'D FILL THIS CHAMBER UP
WITH GUNPOWDER.
THEN ONCE THE CHAMBER'S
FILLED UP,
YOU'D DROP A CORK DOWN
THE STANDPIPE, OR SOME STOPPER.
WHEN THE TRIPWIRES SECURED
TO THE COLLAR
ARE DISTURBED
BY A GRAVE ROBBER...
THE THING GOES KA-BOOM!
WOW, I WOULD SAY
THAT'S THE SAME DEVICE.
BECAUSE HIS DEVICE
HAS NO MARKINGS ON IT
AND BECAUSE IT'S NOT
AN EXACT MATCH,
HENRY MAY HAVE A PROTOTYPE
OF HOWELL'S PATENTED
GRAVE TORPEDO.
IT'S SO CLOSE THAT
IT'S GOT TO BE IT.
IT'S GOT TO BE.
YOU GUYS REALLY
DID A JOB ON THIS.
THIS IS WORTH KNOWING.
THIS IS -- I MEAN,
THIS IS HISTORY.
WELL, THIS HAS BEEN
A GREAT INVESTIGATION,
AND I REALLY APPRECIATE YOU
BRINGING THIS TO ME.
YOU'RE RIGHT
ON THE BALL, WES.
PUT 'ER THERE, PAL.
IN 1881, THE YEAR HOWELL'S
GRAVE TORPEDO WAS PATENTED,
OHIO ENACTED
THE ANATOMY LAW.
IT PERMITTED MEDICAL SCHOOLS
TO USE UNCLAIMED BODIES
FROM PUBLIC INSTITUTIONS.
BY THE TURN OF THE CENTURY,
BODY SNATCHING CASES
HAD SIGNIFICANTLY DECLINED.
CADAVER STORAGE AND
PRESERVATION IMPROVED,
ALLOWING SCHOOLS
TO ACCUMULATE BODIES,
AND THE NEED FOR STEALING
FRESH HUMAN CORPSES
WAS A THING OF THE PAST.
EVEN PRESIDENTIAL BURIAL SITES
WERE PREY FOR GRAVE ROBBERS.
ELEVEN YEARS AFTER
ABRAHAM LINCOLN'S ASSASSINATION,
A CRIMINAL GANG HATCHED A PLOT
TO RANSOM HIS CORPSE.
THEY WANTED $200,000
AND THE RELEASE
OF AN IMPRISONED COHORT.
ON ELECTION NIGHT 1876, THE
THIEVES RAIDED LINCOLN'S TOMB
IN SPRINGFIELD, ILLINOIS.
BUT THE 500-POUND
CEDAR AND LEAD COFFIN
WAS TOO HEAVY TO MOVE.
TIPPED-OFF SECRET SERVICE AGENTS
ARRIVED IN TIME
TO CATCH THE WOULD-BE
GRAVE ROBBERS IN THE ACT.
AFTER THE ATTEMPTED ROBBERY,
THE NATIONAL LINCOLN
MONUMENT SOCIETY
SECRETLY MOVED LINCOLN'S CORPSE
TO ANOTHER PART OF THE TOMB.
FOR YEARS, THE PUBLIC PAID
THEIR RESPECTS
TO AN EMPTY SARCOPHAGUS.
BEFORE LINCOLN'S BODY WAS LAID
TO ITS FINAL RESTING PLACE,
IT WAS EXHUMED
AND CHECKED TWICE
TO MAKE SURE THE CORPSE
WAS STILL THERE.
AS A LAST SAFETY MEASURE,
IN 1901, PRESIDENT
AND MRS. LINCOLN'S BODIES
WERE ENCASED IN LEAD.
THEIR COFFINS WERE CAGED
IN STEEL
AND BURIED BENEATH
10 FEET OF CEMENT,
ENSURING THAT LINCOLN WOULD STAY
IN SPRINGFIELD FOREVER.
Tukufu:
BE A HISTORY DETECTIVE
YOURSELF.
HISTORY DETECTIVES WILL RETURN
IN A MOMENT, BUT FIRST...
GO TO pbs.org
AND LEARN MORE ABOUT
INVESTIGATIVE TECHNIQUES
OR SUBMIT YOUR OWN MYSTERY
TO THE TEAM.
YOU CAN ALSO FIND OUT MORE
ABOUT TONIGHT'S INVESTIGATIONS
ONLY AT pbs.org.
THIS EPISODE OF HISTORY
DETECTIVES IS AVAILABLE ON DVD.
THE COMPANION BOOK TO THE
PROGRAM IS ALSO AVAILABLE.
TO ORDER,
CALL PBS HOME VIDEO AT...
OR VISIT US ONLINE AT...
Captions by LNS Captioning
Portland, Oregon
www.LNScaptioning.com
Elvis Costello:
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ IT'S JUST LIKE
WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
Gwendolyn:
THIS PROGRAM WAS MADE POSSIBLE
BY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO YOUR PBS STATION
FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.