WE'RE THE HISTORY DETECTIVES,
AND WE'RE GOING TO INVESTIGATE
SOME UNTOLD STORIES
FROM AMERICA'S PAST.
Gwendolyn:
THIS WEEK,
THIS NAVY SCHOONER
ONCE FLEW THE FLAG
IN A BORDER DISPUTE
WITH THE MIGHTY BRITISH EMPIRE.
ARE THESE HER
LAST REMAINS?
OH, MY.
Elyse:
HOW IS THIS CONNECTICUT
FARMHOUSE CONNECTED
TO THE ASSASSINATION
OF A RUSSIAN CZAR?
Tukufu:
AND IS THIS PAINTING
AN UNKNOWN WORK
BY AN IMMIGRANT POET
WHOSE WORDS INSPIRED
AN AMERICAN GENERATION?
People chanting:
END THE WAR! END THE WAR!
Elvis Costello:
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ I GET SO ANGRY
WHEN THE TEARDROPS START ♪
♪ BUT HE CAN'T BE WOUNDED
'CAUSE HE'S GOT NO HEART ♪
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ IT'S JUST LIKE
WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
Gwendolyn:
THIS PROGRAM WAS MADE POSSIBLE
BY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO YOUR PBS STATION
FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.
OUR FIRST STORY INVESTIGATES
A MARITIME MYSTERY
WASHED UP ON
AN OREGON BEACH.
1846: TENSIONS BETWEEN
THE U.S. AND BRITAIN
ARE APPROACHING
A BOILING POINT.
ALL EYES ARE FOCUSED
ON THE DISPUTED BORDER
BETWEEN THE U.S.
AND THE BRITISH COLONIAL
TERRITORY OF CANADA.
AT STAKE IS OWNERSHIP
OF THE ENORMOUS RICHES
OF SOME 300,000 SQUARE MILES
OF THE PACIFIC NORTHWEST.
THE U.S. NEEDS
RECONNAISSANCE
AND DISPATCHES
AN ARMED NAVAL VESSEL,
THE USS SHARK.
BUT THAT SEPTEMBER,
DISASTER STRIKES.
THE SHARK WRECKS
AND SINKS
AT THE TREACHEROUS MOUTH
OF THE COLUMBIA RIVER.
MORE THAN A CENTURY
AND A HALF LATER,
14-YEAR-OLD
MIRANDA PETRONE
FROM TUALATIN, OREGON,
THINKS SHE MAY HAVE FOUND
A PIECE OF THIS
HISTORIC SHIP.
ME AND MY DAD WERE WALKING
ALONG THE BEACH,
AND I SAW THIS BIG THING
WITH RUST,
AND I'M LIKE,
"HEY, DAD, COME HERE."
HI.
I'M GWEN WRIGHT,
NICE TO MEET YOU.
SO I HEAR YOU FOUND SOMETHING
PRETTY INTERESTING AROUND HERE.
YEAH, I DID.
WHAT WAS IT?
I FOUND A CANNON.
NOW, ARE YOU SURE
IT WAS A CANNON?
WELL, NOT AT FIRST.
ME AND MY DAD WERE WALKING
ALONG THE BEACH
AND THERE WAS THIS
BIG BLACK ROCKY THING,
SO I WENT UP A LITTLE CLOSER
AND EVENTUALLY SAW RUST.
I THOUGHT, "ROCKS AREN'T
SUPPOSED TO HAVE RUST,"
AND SO I CALLED
MY DAD OVER.
HE CAME AND
CHECKED IT OUT.
HE WAS LIKE, "HUH,
MAYBE IT'S A CANNON."
HE WAS JUST JOKING, THOUGH,
BUT I STILL WENT OUT THERE,
AND IT WAS, SO...
NOW, I'M HOPING THOSE ARE
SOME PICTURES YOU TOOK.
IS THAT RIGHT?
YES.
SO THIS IS YOU.
ARE THESE YOUR SISTERS
OR FRIENDS?
WELL, THAT ONE'S MY SISTER
AND THAT ONE'S MY FRIEND.
WHAT DID YOU NOTICE, ACTUALLY,
WAS IT THIS RUST HERE?
YEAH, I WALKED UP CLOSER
AND SAW THERE WAS RUST.
AND THEN THIS FRIEND OF OURS
FOUND THE SECOND ONE.
MIRANDA'S FRIEND MADE
A SIMILAR FIND,
ANOTHER BIG
STONE-COVERED OBJECT.
WAS IT IN THE SAME PLACE?
UM, NO, IT WAS PROBABLY
A LITTLE BIT FARTHER OUT.
MIRANDA'S DISCOVERY GENERATED
A LOT OF LOCAL EXCITEMENT.
THE MEDIA SPECULATED
SHE'D FOUND A RELIC
FROM THE SHIPWRECK OF AN OLD
NAVY VESSEL CALLED THE SHARK.
IT WAS MADE IN 1821,
AND IT CRASHED IN 1846
AROUND THIS AREA.
WHAT DID YOU DO NEXT?
MY DAD, HE LOOKED
AT THIS BOOK,
AND IT SHOWED PICTURES
OF THE SHARK,
KIND OF LOOKED AT THEM,
WE WERE LIKE,
"OKAY, WELL, THIS HAS
SOME SIMILARITIES."
MIRANDA'S RESEARCH
INDICATED
THAT THE SHARK SANK
IN THE COLUMBIA RIVER
60 TO 75 MILES
NORTH OF HERE
AND THAT SOME WRECKAGE
COULD HAVE DRIFTED SOUTH
TO THIS BEACH.
CAN YOU TELL ME EXACTLY WHAT
YOU'D LIKE FOR ME TO FIND OUT?
I'D LIKE TO FIND OUT
IF IT REALLY IS A CANNON
AND IF IT REALLY DID
COME FROM THE SHARK.
I'LL SEE WHAT I CAN FIND
FOR YOU, OKAY?
OKAY.
WHATEVER IT IS SHE'S FOUND
IS NOW BEING PROTECTED
BY THE OREGON PARKS
AND RECREATION DEPARTMENT
AT NEHALEM BAY
STATE PARK.
HI, ARE YOU CHRIS HAVEL?
I AM.
GWEN WRIGHT,
SO NICE TO MEET YOU.
CHRIS HAVEL IS
THE PROJECT COORDINATOR
FOR THE DEPARTMENT'S
CANNON CONSERVATION.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
OH, MY.
IT'S ACTUALLY BEAUTIFUL,
ALL THESE COLORS.
WELL, I CAN SEE THAT THIS ONE
CERTAINLY LOOKS LIKE A CANNON,
ALTHOUGH THE OTHER ONE,
NOT AT ALL.
SO WHAT IS THIS STUFF
THAT'S ALL OVER IT
BEYOND THE ROCKS
AND STONES I CAN SEE?
WELL, THESE ARE CONCRETIONS.
THIS IS A NATURAL FORM
OF CONCRETE
THAT FORMS AROUND ANYTHING
THAT'S LEFT ON THE OCEAN SHORE
IN CONTACT WITH THE SAND
FOR A LONG PERIOD OF TIME.
DOES THIS KIND OF CONCRETION
GIVE YOU ANY IDEA ABOUT AGE?
IT'S DIFFICULT TO TELL THE AGE
JUST BASED ON THE CONCRETION.
THE KIND OF CHEMICALS THAT ARE
ON THE BEACH, THE WEATHERING,
HOW MUCH WATER IS THERE,
THE SALINITY,
ALL OF THESE THINGS
CAN AFFECT HOW QUICKLY
THE CONCRETIONS
BUILD UP.
CHRIS SAYS
MIRANDA'S DISCOVERY
HAS THE DEPARTMENT EXCITED
BECAUSE 100 YEARS AGO,
ANOTHER CANNON, ALSO PRESUMED
TO BE FROM THE USS SHARK,
WAS RETRIEVED FROM
THE VERY SAME BEACH.
I'VE GOT A DRAWING HERE.
CHRIS COMPARES THE SOAKING MASS
OF SEDIMENT AND RUST
TO A DIAGRAM OF A
SHARK-ERA CARRONADE,
OR SHORT-BARRELED CANNON, THAT
COULD BE HIDDEN BENEATH IT.
BUT IF I'M TO DETERMINE
WHETHER MIRANDA'S CANNON
IS FROM THE USS SHARK,
I'LL NEED TO LEARN
ALL I CAN ABOUT THE SHIP,
STARTING WITH
ITS FINAL VOYAGE.
I'M RETRACING
THE SHARK'S ROUTE
UP THE COLUMBIA RIVER
TO FORT VANCOUVER,
WHERE THE SHIP ANCHORED
WHEN IT FIRST ARRIVED
IN THE PACIFIC NORTHWEST.
THE FORT, NOW IN
WASHINGTON STATE,
THEN OPERATED UNDER
AN ENGLISH CHARTER
AND BELONGED TO
THE HUDSON'S BAY COMPANY,
THE FIRST CORPORATION
IN NORTH AMERICA.
GREG SHINE
IS CHIEF RANGER.
WELCOME TO FORT VANCOUVER.
HERE'S AN IMAGE
OF THE SHARK.
THE SHARK WAS A SCHOONER,
AND SHE WAS LAUNCHED IN 1821.
AND A FORE-AND-AFT
RIGGED SCHOONER,
WHICH MEANT IT HAD TWO MASTS
HERE SLIGHTLY RAKED BACK.
THE SHARK WAS
WELL-ARMED,
HAVING POLICED
WEST AFRICAN WATERS
AGAINST THE SLAVE TRADE,
SAFELY CONDUCTED FREED SLAVES
TO NEWLY FOUNDED LIBERIA,
AND PROTECTED
AMERICAN MERCHANTS
AGAINST PIRATES
IN THE CARIBBEAN.
BUT I CAN'T SEE ANY CANNONS
IN THIS PICTURE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MANY
SHE WAS CARRYING?
YES, THE SHARK
HAD TEN CARRONADES
AND TWO LONG GUNS, AND THESE
LITTLE OPEN AREAS HERE
WERE CANNON PORTS.
THIS EXPERIENCED SHIP
WAS CHOSEN TO SAIL
FOR THE PACIFIC NORTHWEST
IN 1846.
AS THE U.S. BORDER DISPUTE
WITH BRITAIN INTENSIFIED,
THE SHARK'S COMMANDER,
LT. NEIL HOWISON,
WAS INSTRUCTED
TO RALLY AMERICANS
WITH A DISPLAY
OF THE FLAG,
SURVEY
THE OREGON TERRITORY,
AND TALK WITH BRITISH
AND AMERICAN HOMESTEADERS
LIVING THERE.
HIS ORDERS WERE
VERY DIRECT:
HE WAS TO COME IN TO
OBTAIN THEIR DISPOSITION,
WHETHER IT WAS FOR THE UNITED
STATES OR FOR GREAT BRITAIN,
AND ALSO TO REPORT
ON THE AGRICULTURE,
THE COMMERCE OF THE AREA,
AND GIVE A GENERAL OVERVIEW
OF THE OREGON COUNTRY.
HOWISON KNEW A MISSTEP
COULD EASILY IGNITE TENSIONS
IN THE AREA.
PRESIDENT POLK'S
DEMOCRATIC PARTY
WAS PUSHING TO LEGITIMIZE
AMERICAN SETTLEMENTS
ACROSS THE CONTINENT.
ONLY A YEAR EARLIER,
IN 1845,
THIS DRIVE WAS DUBBED
"MANIFEST DESTINY,"
IMPLYING THAT IT
WAS GOD'S WILL
FOR THE UNITED STATES
TO EXPAND ACROSS THE CONTINENT
WEST TO THE PACIFIC,
SOUTH INTO LATIN AMERICA,
AND NORTH INTO
BRITISH CANADA.
THIS BELIEF HELPED INFLAME
THE POLITICAL RALLYING CRY
OF "54-40 OR FIGHT,"
A CALL TO EXTEND
AMERICA'S REACH
THROUGH BRITISH CANADA
ALL THE WAY
TO LATITUDE 54 DEGREES
AND 40 MINUTES.
THE OREGON SETTLERS NEEDED
LITTLE ENCOURAGEMENT.
THERE WERE CERTAINLY
SOME AMERICAN SETTLERS
THAT WERE HERE THAT WERE
CROSSING THE COLUMBIA RIVER
AND BEGINNING
TO HOMESTEAD,
OR, IN THE EYES
OF THE HUDSON'S BAY COMPANY,
JUMPED LAND CLAIMS
THAT THE HUDSON'S BAY COMPANY
HAD ESTABLISHED.
WHAT WAS THE BRITISH RESPONSE
TO THE SHARK ARRIVING?
THE HUDSON'S BAY COMPANY
WELCOMED THE SHARK
AND LT. HOWISON
AND WELCOMED AN AMERICAN SHIP
INTO THE COLUMBIA RIVER
BECAUSE THEY PROVIDED
SOME LAW AND ORDER,
REALLY,
TO AN AREA THAT DIDN'T HAVE
MUCH LAW AND ORDER.
WITH THE LAND
AND TEMPERAMENT SURVEYED,
HOWISON SET SAIL
FOR SAN FRANCISCO
TO FILE HIS REPORT.
WHEN THEY LEFT
FORT VANCOUVER,
THEY WERE ALREADY
BEHIND SCHEDULE.
THE WINTER CAN BE
VERY FEROCIOUS,
AND ESPECIALLY
AT THE MOUTH OF THE RIVER
NEAR THE COLUMBIA RIVER BAR.
AS THE SHARK
HEADED FOR OPEN SEAS,
IT WRECKED ON
AN UNCHARTED SANDBAR
AT THE MOUTH
OF THE COLUMBIA.
LUCKILY, ALL OF THE PERSONNEL
WERE ABLE TO SURVIVE.
GREG SHOWS ME HOWISON'S
REPORT TO THE U.S. CONGRESS.
ONE PASSAGE MAY RELATE DIRECTLY
TO MIRANDA'S DISCOVERY.
IT SAYS HOWISON IS EAGER
TO RECOVER
THE SHIP'S
LOST WEAPONS.
"RECEIVING INFORMATIONS
THAT PART OF THE HULL
"WITH GUNS UPON IT
HAD COME ASHORE,
"I SENT MIDSHIPMAN SIMES,
AN ENTERPRISING YOUTH,
TO VISIT THE SPOT."
IN THE WATER
JUST OFF THE BEACH,
SIMES FOUND
A BROKEN SECTION OF DECK
WITH THREE OF THE SHARK'S
ONE-TON CARRONADES.
"HE SUCCEEDED IN GETTING ONE
ABOVE THE HIGH-WATER MARK,
"BUT THE OTHER TWO
WERE INACCESSIBLE
ON ACCOUNT OF THE SURF."
GREG SAYS
THE RESCUED CARRONADE
WAS DRAGGED
TOWARD THE SHORE
BUT HAD TO BE ABANDONED.
IN 1898, IT WAS REDISCOVERED
AFTER A STORM
AND IS NOW ON EXHIBIT
AT THE CANNON BEACH
HISTORICAL SOCIETY MUSEUM.
DID MIRANDA DISCOVER
ONE OF THE TWO
LEFT IN THE SURF?
EOLOGIST
DENNIS GRIFFIN
SAYS THE COLUMBIA RIVER
WAS A NOTORIOUS GRAVEYARD
FOR HUNDREDS OF SHIPS,
NOT JUST THE SHARK.
WHAT WE SEE TODAY IS A SMALL
GLIMPSE OF WHAT IT ONCE WAS.
IT WAS THE MIGHTY COLUMBIA
BEFORE ALL THE DAMS.
BUT THE MOUTH OF THE COLUMBIA
WAS A VERY WICKED PLACE.
YOU HAD TIDES COMING UP THERE
OR STORMS COMING UP THERE
FROM 35 TO 50 FEET WAVES
TO CRASH.
FIFTY FEET WAVES!
HUGE WAVES.
THEY CALL THIS THE
GRAVEYARD OF THE PACIFIC.
THE MOUTH OF THE RIVER
WAS KNOWN TO BE DANGEROUS,
BUT DENNIS SAYS IF YOU WANTED
A PIECE OF THE REGION'S WEALTH,
YOU HAD TO RUN
THE COLUMBIA'S GAUNTLET.
YOU HAD THE HUDSON'S BAY COMPANY
IN CANADA
COMING ACROSS FOR FURS.
LOTS AND LOTS
OF SALMON.
SAN FRANCISCO AND THE
BIG CITIES, THEY NEEDED WOOD.
PEOPLE CAME UP THE COAST,
FOUND LOTS OF TREES.
ALL THAT SHIP TRAFFIC MEANT
A LOT OF WRECKS OVER THE YEARS.
OF THE 308 I KNOW, I HAVE 104
THAT I THINK WERE WRECKED
EITHER AT THE MOUTH
OF THE COLUMBIA
AND DOWN TO ARCH CAPE,
IN THAT AREA.
NOW, OF THOSE 104,
WE HAVE TO NARROW IT DOWN,
WHICH ONES CARRIED CANNON,
AND WE DON'T KNOW THAT,
AND THAT'S A BIG IMPORTANT PART.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
ARE THE ODDS
THAT THE CANNONS WE HAVE
ARE FROM THE SHARK?
EVERYONE WANTS TO SAY
IT'S THE SHARK.
I KNOW.
AND I'D LIKE TO THINK
OF IT BEING THE SHARK,
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW.
DENNIS SUGGESTS THE RECOVERED
SHARK CARRONADE
COULD HELP RESOLVE
OUR MYSTERY.
I'M MEETING COLUMBIA RIVER
MARITIME MUSEUM CURATOR
DAVID PEARSON
FOR A CLOSER LOOK.
SO THIS IS IT, THE CANNON
THAT WAS FOUND IN 1898?
THIS IS IT, RIGHT,
JANUARY OF 1898.
DAVE SAYS THIS CANNON WAS
RECOVERED ON THE SAME BEACH,
ABOUT 200 FEET FROM WHERE
MIRANDA MADE HER DISCOVERY.
WAS THIS THE ORIGINAL BASE,
BY THE WAY?
THIS ONE THAT WE'RE LOOKING AT
HERE IS ACTUALLY A REPRODUCTION
FROM NAVAL DRAWINGS
THAT ARE WELL KNOWN.
IF MIRANDA'S DISCOVERY
HAS A SIMILAR BASE,
THAT WOULD CONFIRM
IT'S A CARRONADE
FROM THE RIGHT ERA,
BUT NOT NECESSARILY THE SHARK
OR EVEN AN AMERICAN SHIP.
THE CARRONADE WAS INVENTED
BY THE BRITISH FOR THEIR NAVY.
THEIR CARRONADE WAS
ACTUALLY ATTACHED
TO THE DECK
OF THE SHIP.
AND IT WOULD ACTUALLY BE
PINNED AT THE FRONT OF IT
AND THEN SWIVEL
ON THAT PIN
TO PREVENT IT FROM MOVING
AROUND ON THE SHIP.
IT WAS THE OLD EXPRESSION,
"LOOSE CANNONS,"
AND THAT WAS EXACTLY IT,
THAT WAS THE LAST THING
YOU WANTED ON A SHIP
HEAVING IN THE WAVES
WAS A CANNON BOUNCING AROUND.
SO THE NAVY TOOK
THE ADDITIONAL STEP
AND WOULD ACTUALLY PIN THEM
TO THE DECK.
DAVE EXPLAINS
HOW THIS WORKED.
A THREADED PIN AT THE BACK
OF THE BARREL
ADJUSTED THE TILT.
THE BARREL WAS MOUNTED ON
A SMALL BASE, OR SLIDER,
WHICH FIT ONTO A LONGER
SLOTTED BOARD.
THIS BOARD SAT ON ROLLERS
AT THE BACK
AND PIVOTED
AT THE FRONT.
ANOTHER PIN BENEATH
THE CARRONADE
WENT FROM THE SLIDER
INTO THE SLOT.
WHEN THE CARRONADE FIRED,
THIS CONTROLLED THE RECOIL.
DAVE SAYS THE RECENT FINDS SHOW
SIMILARITIES TO THIS DESIGN.
THEY STILL HAVE THAT SLIDER
ATTACHED TO IT,
OR AT LEAST EVIDENCE
OF THAT.
THAT BRINGS THE PROBABILITY
OF THIS BEING A U.S. NAVY SHIP
MUCH, MUCH HIGHER
IN OUR EYES.
BUT WITH ALL THE CONCRETION
SURROUNDING MIRANDA'S OBJECT,
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO MAKE
A DEFINITIVE CONNECTION.
MY INVESTIGATION
MIGHT BE AT AN END.
BUT BECAUSE INTEREST
IN MIRANDA'S FIND IS HIGH,
I'VE BEEN ABLE TO SCHEDULE AN
X-RAY SESSION FOR THE CANNONS.
I'M RETURNING TO NEHALEM BAY
TO MEET ROBERT NEYLAND,
HEAD OF THE UNDERWATER
ARCHEOLOGY BRANCH
OF THE NAVAL
HISTORICAL CENTER,
WHO WILL EXAMINE
THE X-RAYS.
THIS IS JUST
A GENERIC CARRONADE.
BOB TELLS ME
THESE WERE COMMON
ON MANY NAVY SHIPS
LIKE THE SHARK
IN THE FIRST HALF
OF THE 19th CENTURY.
IN A CLOSE-IN FIGHT,
THEY WOULD DO MORE DAMAGE
TO THE OPPOSING
OR THE ENEMY SHIP
AND DO MORE DAMAGE
TO THE CREWS, TOO.
IT WOULD SMASH UP THE WOOD
OR THE SHIP A LOT MORE.
BECAUSE THIS SMALL CANNON
WAS A POPULAR WEAPON,
BOB SAYS MATCHING IT
TO THE SHARK WILL BE TOUGH.
BUT ONCE THE X-RAYS
HAVE PENETRATED
MORE THAN 150 YEARS
OF DEPOSITS,
THEY MAY REVEAL
SOMETHING TELLING.
YOU COULD GET LUCKY AND ACTUALLY
SEE A DATE MARKED ON THE GUNS
AS WELL AS FOUNDRY MARKS.
YOU COULD GET LUCKY
AND SEE THAT.
THAT'D BE VERY LUCKY.
YEAH, IT WOULD BE.
YOU KNOW, OR SAY "U.S. NAVY"
AS WELL, TOO.
TO CAPTURE A GLIMPSE OF THE
OBJECT BENEATH THIS THICK MASS
REQUIRES AN EXTREMELY
HIGH-POWERED SYSTEM.
A TEAM OF SPECIALISTS
IN NUCLEAR IMAGING
FROM FUJIFILM NDT
AND PSI INCORPORATED
ARE VOLUNTEERING
THEIR EXPERTISE TO HELP.
BOB EXAMINES MIRANDA'S CANNON
TO PLAN THE X-RAYS.
HERE YOU'VE GOT YOUR PIN
FOR THE CARRIAGE.
THIS APPEARS TO BE WHAT'S LEFT
OF YOUR BREACH RING,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE
A PIECE OF IT'S BROKEN OFF
IF I'M CORRECT IN THAT.
THE SCREW,
THE ELEVATING SCREW,
SHOULD BE RIGHT IN HERE
SOMEWHERE AS WELL, TOO.
YOU GUYS ARE GOING
TO HAVE TO BACK OFF.
IT'S GOING TO GET
REAL HOT RIGHT HERE.
THE FILM NEEDS TO BE EXPOSED
FOR NEARLY 90 MINUTES
TO CAPTURE ENOUGH DETAIL.
WHEN ALL OF THE EXPOSURES
ARE FINALLY COMPLETE,
WE TAKE THE X-RAY PLATES
INSIDE TO SEE WHAT WE HAVE.
STILL NOT GETTING
ANYTHING, HUH?
I CAN SEE A LITTLE MORE.
THE FIRST IMAGE
REVEALS LITTLE.
THE SECOND PLATE IS
ONLY SLIGHTLY BETTER,
BUT IT DOES OUTLINE
THE SHAPE OF A CANNON BARREL.
IN THIS SHOT, WE'VE GOT
SOME OF THE BORE,
WE'RE DEFINITELY LOOKING AT
THE BANDING AROUND THE GUN...
THE BANDING KEPT THE BARREL
FROM RUPTURING WHEN FIRED.
WE'RE DOWN
TO THE LAST PLATE.
THAT IS A GREAT SHOT.
NOW WE'RE TALKING.
IT'S TIME TO GIVE
MIRANDA HER ANSWER.
I HAVE DONE ALL THE RESEARCH
THAT WAS POSSIBLE
ON THE CANNON
THAT YOU FOUND.
BUT THIS IS NOT
JUST A CANNON,
IT'S A CERTAIN KIND OF CANNON
CALLED A CARRONADE
THAT WAS ON U.S. NAVY SHIPS
IN THE EARLY HALF
OF THE 19th CENTURY.
I TELL MIRANDA ABOUT
THE USS SHARK'S ROLE
IN THE SHAPING
OF AMERICA'S BORDERS
AND ITS FOREIGN RELATIONS.
ONLY VERY POWERFUL X-RAYS
COULD PEER DEEP
INTO THE MASS OF SEDIMENT
AND RUSTED METAL
TO REVEAL WHAT LIES
UNDERNEATH.
SO WHAT ARE WE
LOOKING AT HERE?
THERE'S YOUR SCREW.
EXCELLENT.
I GUESS THIS IS THE THREADING
ON IT, RIGHT?
YOU CAN CLEARLY SEE
YOU'VE STILL GOT THE THREADS
VERY VISIBLE IN HERE.
OH, THAT'S WHERE
YOU'D CRANK IT, OKAY.
THE LOOP HERE
FOR THE BREACH ROPE,
A LONG GUN WOULDN'T
HAVE THAT.
THE ELEVATING SCREW,
A LONG GUN WOULD NOT HAVE
AN ELEVATING SCREW.
IT'S DEFINITELY
A CARRONADE.
BUT IT ALSO COMPARES
VERY FAVORABLY
TO THE CANNON THAT
WAS RECOVERED IN THE 1890s
AND IS NOW AN EXHIBIT,
SO SUGGESTING IT IS
THE SAME TIME OF CANNON,
PERHAPS FROM THE SAME SHIP.
I DON'T SEE ANYWHERE
WHERE IT SAYS "USS SHARK"
OR "U.S. NAVY,"
BUT THIS IS ALL CONSISTENT
WITH THE CARRONADE.
SO FAR, CIRCUMSTANTIAL
EVIDENCE, IT IS CONSISTENT
WITH WHAT WE'D EXPECT TO SEE
FOR A CARRONADE FROM THE SHARK.
AND HERE IS AN X-RAY
OF THE PART OF THE CANNON
THAT WOULD GO INTO
THE DECK THERE.
YOU WOULD SCREW IT
TO LIFT IT UP.
THAT'S AWESOME.
THANK YOU.
ALL THE PEOPLE AGREE THAT
WHILE WE'LL NEVER KNOW FOR SURE,
YOU PROBABLY FOUND THE CANNON
THAT WAS ON THE USS SHARK.
NICE, THAT'S PRETTY COOL.
DON'T YOU FEEL PROUD ABOUT THAT?
YEAH, THAT'S COOL.
YOU FOUND SOMETHING
THAT DOESN'T JUST GIVE US
A CRITICAL PART OF
THE EARLY HISTORY OF OREGON
BUT TELLS US ABOUT
A VERY IMPORTANT PART
OF AMERICAN HISTORY.
WOW, ONE CANNON.
YEAH.
THE GREAT IRONY
OF THE SHARK'S STORY
WAS THAT A TREATY
ENDING THE DISPUTE
OVER THE CANADIAN BORDER
WAS SIGNED IN JUNE OF 1846,
ONE MONTH BEFORE THE SHARK
ARRIVED AT THE COLUMBIA RIVER.
NEWS DIDN'T REACH
LIEUTENANT HOWISON
UNTIL A MONTH
AFTER THE SHARK SANK.
THE OREGON TREATY SET
THE U.S./CANADIAN BORDER
AT THE 49th PARALLEL,
WHERE IT REMAINS TODAY.
SOME OF THE WORLD'S MOST
FASCINATING HISTORICAL OBJECTS
HAVE EMERGED
FROM THE DEEP.
OCEANS, RIVERS, AND LAKES
ARE TOMBS
FOR AN INCALCULABLE WEALTH
OF OBJECTS.
ALTHOUGH UNDERWATER RECOVERY
IS NOT ALWAYS EASY,
ADVANCES IN TECHNOLOGY
HAVE MADE MARITIME ARCHEOLOGY
AN EXCITING NEW FRONTIER
FOR HISTORIANS.
IN 1943, JACQUES COUSTEAU
AND EMILE GAGNON
REVOLUTIONIZED
UNDERWATER EXPLORATION
WITH THEIR AQUA-LUNG,
A SELF-CONTAINED UNDERWATER
BREATHING APPARATUS.
THIS SCUBA DEVICE
ALLOWED HUMANS TO FREELY DIVE
TO DEPTHS OF 180 FEET.
THE NEXT GREAT ADVANCE
WAS TITANIUM-REINFORCED
SUBMERSIBLES,
WHICH COULD PROBE TWO AND
A HALF MILES BELOW SEA LEVEL.
IN 1985,
AN UNMANNED SUBMERSIBLE
FINALLY MADE CONTACT
WITH THE TITANIC.
THE NOTION THAT A GREAT GASH
HAD RIPPED THE SHIP IN TWO
WAS NOW DEBUNKED.
IN 2002, ONE OF HISTORY'S
MOST SIGNIFICANT DISCOVERIES
WAS MADE
BY SHEER ACCIDENT.
OFF INDIA'S COAST,
OCEANOGRAPHERS UNEARTHED
WHAT COULD BE ONE OF THE
WORLD'S OLDEST CIVILIZATIONS.
SCIENTISTS USED SONAR
TO IDENTIFY
HUGE GEOMETRIC STRUCTURES
DATING BACK 10,000 YEARS.
Elyse:
OUR NEXT STORY
INVESTIGATES
A CONNECTICUT FARMHOUSE
WITH AN UNSETTLED PAST.
AS THE 20th CENTURY DAWNS,
AMERICA'S CITIES
ARE INDUSTRIALIZING
AND GROWING AT
AN EXPLOSIVE RATE.
THEY'RE BEING FILLED
BY A TIDAL WAVE
OF IMMIGRANTS FROM EUROPE
AND NATIVE-BORN AMERICANS
WHO ARE ABANDONING
THEIR FAMILY FARMS
FOR THE OPPORTUNITY
AND BETTER WAGES
OF THE INDUSTRIAL REVOLUTION.
MORE THAN 100 YEARS LATER,
CHRIS REMY OF EAST HADDAM,
CONNECTICUT,
BELIEVES HIS HOME
MAY SOMEHOW BE CONNECTED
TO THIS DRAMATIC PERIOD
IN AMERICA'S PAST.
I'D LIKE TO KNOW
A LITTLE BIT MORE
ABOUT THE HISTORY
OF MY HOUSE,
WHO WERE THE PEOPLE
THAT LIVED HERE.
HI.
I'M ELYSE.
CHRIS, COME ON IN.
WHAT A GREAT HOUSE.
THANK YOU.
SO HOW LONG HAVE YOU
OWNED IT?
WE BOUGHT THE HOUSE
SIX YEARS AGO.
IT'S FIVE ACRES, PART OF WHAT
WAS ORIGINALLY A 60-ACRE FARM.
THIS IS THE MAP FROM
WHEN THEY SUBDIVIDED IT
BACK IN THE '70s,
AND HERE'S OUR FIVE-ACRE PLOT
RIGHT HERE.
WHAT SPARKED YOUR INTEREST
IN DOING RESEARCH?
WELL, I KNEW THE HOUSE
WAS BUILT IN 1804, OBVIOUSLY,
WHEN I BOUGHT IT,
SO I WANTED TO RESEARCH
WHAT I COULD FIND OUT,
WHO BUILT IT AND WHEN,
AND WHO'S LIVED HERE.
WHAT'D YOU FIND OUT?
WELL, I FOUND OUT THAT AROUND
THE TURN OF THE LAST CENTURY,
THE PROPERTY SEEMED TO
CHANGE HANDS A LOT OF TIMES --
EVERY YEAR,
EVERY TWO YEARS --
FOR A GOOD 15, 20 YEARS,
AND THEY SEEMED TO HAVE RUSSIAN
AND EASTERN-EUROPEAN NAMES.
WHAT SPECIFICALLY
DO YOU WANT ME TO FIND OUT?
I'D LIKE TO KNOW
WHO THESE PEOPLE WERE,
WHAT WERE THEY
DOING HERE...
MM-HMM.
AND WHY DID THE PROPERTY
CHANGE HANDS SO MANY TIMES
IN SUCH A SHORT
TIME FRAME?
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING ELSE
FOR ME TO GO ON?
WELL, WHEN I WAS DOING
SOME REMODELING ON THE HOUSE,
INSIDE THE WALLS, I FOUND
THIS OLD WALLPAPER.
ON THE OTHER SIDE IS NEWSPAPER
WITH HEBREW CHARACTERS.
AND AT THE TOP OF THIS PAGE
YOU CAN SEE
IT'S THE JEWISH
MORNING JOURNAL.
WELL, I'M GOING TO GO WALK
OUTSIDE AND TAKE A LOOK AROUND,
AND THEN I GUESS I'M OFF
TO THE TOWN HALL.
OKAY.
I'M ESPECIALLY INTERESTED
IN THIS STORY.
MY OWN FAMILY ARRIVED
FROM EASTERN EUROPE
AND SETTLED IN NEW YORK CITY
AND BALTIMORE, MARYLAND,
THREE GENERATIONS AGO.
BUT IT'S NOT CLEAR WHY SO MANY
EASTERN-EUROPEAN IMMIGRANTS --
IF THAT'S WHAT
THEY WERE --
ROTATED THROUGH THIS FARMHOUSE
AT THE TURN OF THE CENTURY.
MY FIRST STOP
IS TOWN HALL.
THERE ARE LAND DEEDS HERE
GOING BACK TWO CENTURIES.
BEFORE I SCOUR
THESE BOUND RECORDS,
I WANT TO LEARN MORE
ABOUT THE OLD NEWSPAPERS
FROM INSIDE THE WALLS
OF THE HOUSE.
THE JEWISH MORNING JOURNAL
WAS APPARENTLY
AN ULTRA-ORTHODOX NEWSPAPER
THAT STARTED PRINTING
IN THE UNITED STATES
IN NEW YORK CITY
IN 1902.
LISTEN TO THIS:
THE PAPER WASN'T WRITTEN
IN HEBREW,
IT WAS ACTUALLY WRITTEN
IN YIDDISH.
YIDDISH IS WRITTEN
WITH HEBREW CHARACTERS,
BUT IT IS DIFFERENT.
IT'S DERIVED FROM
THE GERMAN LANGUAGE.
THERE'S PROBABLY ONLY
A QUARTER-MILLION PEOPLE
IN THE UNITED STATES
TODAY THAT SPEAK YIDDISH,
INCLUDING MY GRANDMOTHER.
I KNOW FROM HER
THAT BACK THEN,
THE LANGUAGE
WAS SPOKEN WIDELY
AMONG JEWISH IMMIGRANTS
FROM EASTERN EUROPE.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE
WHAT THE LAND DEEDS CAN TELL US.
HERE'S THE FIRST RECORD
OF THE SALE OF THE LAND.
ON JULY 17, 1798,
JUSTIN WORTHINGTON SOLD THE LAND
TO CIRUS WILLEY.
THE FARM STAYED IN
THE SAME HANDS
FOR MORE THAN THREE-QUARTERS
OF A CENTURY.
THE WILLEY FAMILY
SOLD THE FARM IN 1878,
AND THE REAL ESTATE
TRANSACTIONS LOOK PRETTY NORMAL
UNTIL 1891.
ON JUNE 15, 1891,
IT LOOKS LIKE THE LAND
WAS SOLD TO DAVID DINSON.
ONLY FOUR MONTHS LATER,
DINSON SELLS THE FARM
TO LEWIS NAMEROV
AND LOUIS NATESZON
OF NEW YORK CITY.
JUST NINE MONTHS AFTER THAT,
IT'S SOLD AGAIN.
BETWEEN 1891 AND 1906, THE
FARM CHANGES HANDS SIX TIMES:
DINSON,
NAMEROV AND NATESZON,
MALLER, BOOX,
KATZ AND KURRIER,
RITTER AND AZWOLENSKY.
AND THE SALE PRICE
OFTEN INCLUDED LIVESTOCK
AND VARIOUS
FARM EQUIPMENT.
SOMETHING ELSE APPEARS
TO LINK THE FAMILIES
WHO PASSED THROUGH
CHRIS'S HOME.
A FEW OF THESE PEOPLE HAVE
MORTGAGES FROM THE SAME LENDERS,
THE BARON de HIRSCH FUND
AND THE JEWISH AGRICULTURAL
AND INDUSTRIAL AID SOCIETY,
BOTH NEW YORK CORPORATIONS.
CENSUS RECORDS CONFIRM SEVERAL
OF THE FARM'S EARLY OWNERS
WERE FROM RUSSIA.
MAX AND GUSSIE MALLER,
OR MULLER AS IT'S WRITTEN
IN THE CENSUS,
CAME TO AMERICA FROM RUSSIA
IN 1886.
AND THE ENTIRE RITTER FAMILY
WAS BORN IN RUSSIA, ALSO.
SO FAR, I HAVE
RUSSIAN IMMIGRANTS
MOVING FROM NEW YORK CITY,
I HAVE A YIDDISH PAPER THAT
WAS PUBLISHED IN NEW YORK CITY,
AND I HAVE LOANS GIVEN
BY TWO CORPORATIONS
IN NEW YORK CITY.
EVERYTHING IS POINTING
TO MANHATTAN.
I'M MEETING IMMIGRATION
HISTORIAN DANIEL SAWYER
AT NEW YORK'S LOWER EAST SIDE
TENEMENT MUSEUM.
DANIEL, I'M INVESTIGATING
THIS FARMHOUSE
THAT'S IN CONNECTICUT,
AND IN THE EARLY 20th CENTURY,
THERE WAS A LOT OF TURNOVER.
THE PEOPLE WERE GENERALLY
COMING FROM NEW YORK CITY,
AND THERE WERE TWO NAMES
ON THE MORTGAGE
THAT I KEPT SEEING
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
THERE WAS THE
BARON de HIRSCH FUND
AND THE JEWISH AGRICULTURAL
AND INDUSTRIAL AID SOCIETY.
WELL, THE BARON de HIRSCH FUND
WAS SET UP IN 1891
BY BARON MAURICE de HIRSCH,
WHO WAS A EUROPEAN JEWISH
PHILANTHROPIST, IN ORDER TO HELP
THE EASTERN-EUROPEAN JEWISH
IMMIGRANTS TO THE UNITED STATES
TO GET ESTABLISHED
IN THEIR NEW HOME.
DANIEL EXPLAINS THAT
IN MARCH 1881,
THE ASSASSINATION OF THE
RUSSIAN CZAR ALEXANDER II
TRIGGERED A MASSIVE JEWISH
MIGRATION TO THE UNITED STATES.
THERE WAS A POPULAR FEELING THAT
THE JEWS HAD BEEN BEHIND THIS,
AND SO THERE WAS
A WAVE OF POGROMS,
WHICH WERE ANTI-JEWISH RIOTS,
IN WHICH MANY PEOPLE
WERE KILLED
AND MUCH PROPERTY
WAS DESTROYED.
OVER THE NEXT DECADE,
MORE THAN 200,000
EASTERN-EUROPEAN JEWS
FLOODED INTO THE MAIN
EAST COAST PORTS,
PARTICULARLY NEW YORK.
BY THE TURN
OF THE CENTURY,
MORE THAN HALF A MILLION
HAD ARRIVED.
SO THEY CAME HERE
SEEKING A BETTER LIFE.
ABSOLUTELY.
CAME HERE SEEKING JOBS
AND A WAY TO MAKE A LIVING.
MANY OF THESE JEWISH
REFUGEES SETTLED
IN NEW YORK CITY'S
LOWER EAST SIDE,
SURROUNDED BY PEOPLE
WHO SHARED
A COMMON BACKGROUND,
FAITH, AND LANGUAGE.
BUT DANIEL EXPLAINS THAT
PACKED INTO THE SLUMS OF ONE
OF THE MOST DENSELY POPULATED
NEIGHBORHOODS ON EARTH,
THE NEW ARRIVALS ALSO
FOUND THEMSELVES AT ODDS
WITH THE ESTABLISHED
AMERICANIZED JEWISH COMMUNITY.
THEY HAD A VERY AMBIVALENT
FEELING TOWARDS THESE NEWCOMERS.
ON THE ONE HAND, THEY FELT
A KINSHIP WITH THESE PEOPLE
AND WANTED TO HELP.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
THEY WERE FOREIGN,
THEY SPOKE YIDDISH,
THEY WERE POOR,
AND THE ESTABLISHED
JEWISH COMMUNITY WAS AFRAID
THAT THEY WOULD REFLECT
BADLY ON THEM,
AND SO THEY FELT
AN ADDED IMPETUS
TO HELP PEOPLE ESTABLISH
THEMSELVES, AMERICANIZE,
AND GET ESTABLISHED
ECONOMICALLY AS WELL.
HOW DOES THE
BARON de HIRSCH FUND
AND THE JEWISH AGRICULTURAL
AND INDUSTRIAL AID SOCIETY
FIT INTO ALL OF THIS?
THE JEWISH AGRICULTURAL
AND INDUSTRIAL AID SOCIETY
WAS A SPIN-OFF OF
THE BARON de HIRSCH FUND,
WHICH PROVIDED PEOPLE
WITH MORTGAGES
WHEN THEY WANTED TO GET
SET UP AS FARMERS
ON THE LAND
AND WITH HOUSES.
HE SAYS OUR DEED HOLDERS
WERE PART OF A PLAN
TO EASE OVERCROWDING
BY RELOCATING JEWS
OUTSIDE OF NEW YORK CITY,
WHERE THEY COULD EARN
A LIVING OFF THE LAND.
BUT HE CAN'T
SHED ANY LIGHT
ON WHO OUR RUSSIAN
IMMIGRANTS WERE
OR WHY SO MANY SEEMED
TO HAVE STAYED
FOR SUCH A BRIEF PERIOD
AT CHRIS'S FARMHOUSE.
THE CENTER
FOR JEWISH HISTORY
HOUSES THE PAPERS
OF THE BARON'S FUND
AND THE JEWISH
AGRICULTURAL SOCIETY.
IN A VOLUME ABOUT
THE SOCIAL CONDITIONS
FACING RUSSIAN JEWS AT
THE TURN OF THE 19th CENTURY,
I DISCOVER THE JEWISH
AGRICULTURAL SOCIETY,
OR J.A.S., SET FAMILIES
UP ON FARMLAND
ALL ACROSS NEW ENGLAND.
"INDIVIDUAL JEWISH FARMERS
ARE SCATTERED
"THROUGH THE NEW ENGLAND
STATES
"AND OWN FARMS IN RHODE ISLAND,
MASSACHUSETTS, CONNECTICUT,
"MAINE, VERMONT,
AND NEW HAMPSHIRE.
"BY FAR THE GREATEST NUMBER
ARE LOCATED IN CONNECTICUT,
"AND THEY HAVE FORMED
THE MOST IMPORTANT SECTION
OF THE JEWISH FARMING COMMUNITY
IN NEW ENGLAND."
THIS IS A LEDGER BOOK
THAT LISTS LOANS
FROM THE BARON de HIRSCH FUND.
LET'S SEE...
AH, CONNECTICUT.
ALTHOUGH THERE'S NO INFORMATION
ON OUR FAMILIES,
THE ORIGINAL
LOAN APPLICATIONS
DESCRIBE HOW THE
LENDING PROCESS WORKED.
SUCCESSFUL APPLICANTS
WERE RUSSIAN JEWS
WHO WERE HEALTHY ENOUGH
TO HANDLE FARM WORK
AND WHO ALSO HAD A LITTLE BIT
OF MONEY TO GET STARTED.
FOR THOSE
WHO DIDN'T QUALIFY,
THE FUND PROVIDED
TRADE SCHOOLS, ENGLISH CLASSES,
AND SCHOLARSHIPS
FOR STUDENTS IN THE CITY.
BUT I'M NOT FINDING
ANY INFORMATION ON OUR FARMERS.
HI.
HI, ELYSE.
I'M MEETING CONNECTICUT
HISTORIAN BRIANN GREENFIELD
AT THE STATE ARCHIVES.
SHE EXPLAINS WHY CONNECTICUT
WAS SUCH A POPULAR CHOICE
FOR THE IMMIGRANT FARMERS.
WELL, THE SHORT ANSWER
IS AVAILABLE LAND.
A LOT OF OLD YANKEE FARMERS
WERE MOVING AWAY FROM THE FARMS.
THEY WERE BEING PULLED
OUT WEST,
WHERE AGRICULTURE
WAS MORE PRODUCTIVE,
OR THEY WERE COMING
TO THE FACTORY JOBS
THAT WERE AVAILABLE
IN THE CITY.
BRIANN TELLS ME THAT
THE STATE WORRIED
ABOUT THE ABANDONED FARM
PROBLEM
AND THE DECLINE
OF RURAL COMMUNITIES.
IN 1892, THEY BEGAN TO PUBLISH
LISTS OF FARMS FOR SALE.
THIS IS A DESCRIPTION
OF FARMS FOR SALE
IN CONNECTICUT THAT
WAS PUBLISHED IN 1899.
SO IT'S A REAL ESTATE
LISTING?
THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
THEY HAVE MAPS, AND THERE ARE
SOME PICTURES IN HERE AS WELL.
THIS IS EVERYTHING
YOU WOULD NEED TO KNOW
ABOUT THE KINDS OF FARMS
THAT YOU WERE LOOKING AT.
THERE'S EVEN SOME
IN EAST HADDAM.
BRIANN EXPLAINS
THE RUSSIAN JEWS
WEREN'T THE ONLY NEWCOMERS
SETTLING THE OLD YANKEE FARMS.
IT WAS ALL SORTS OF
DIFFERENT IMMIGRANT GROUPS,
AND THIS WAS A PERIOD
OF HEAVY IMMIGRATION.
TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS ARTICLE.
"ALIEN INVASION
OF CONNECTICUT FARMS."
"EVERY THIRD FARM IN CONNECTICUT
IS NOW IN THE HANDS
OF A MAN OF FOREIGN BIRTH."
"THERE IS NO CORNER
OF THE STATE
"INTO WHICH THE IMMIGRANT
FOREIGNER HAS NOT PENETRATED
"AND THAT HE COMES FROM
LANDS THE POLES APART
IN CUSTOMS, LANGUAGE,
RELIGION, AND MORALITY."
THAT SEEMS PRETTY
NEGATIVE TO ME.
WELL, TO BE VERY HONEST,
I THINK THEY SAW IT
AS BOTH A BLESSING
AND AS A THREAT.
A BLESSING BECAUSE
THEY NEEDED AGRICULTURAL LABOR,
BUT ALSO A THREAT
BECAUSE PEOPLE FEARED
THE LOSS OF YANKEE CULTURE.
THE FAMILIES WHO LIVED
IN CHRIS'S HOME
SWAPPED THE OVERCROWDING
AND CLASS TENSION
OF THE JEWISH COMMUNITY
IN NEW YORK
FOR THE XENOPHOBIA
OF THE YANKEES IN CONNECTICUT.
DOES THAT EXPLAIN
WHY THE ARRIVALS
ONLY STAYED FOR
SUCH A SHORT TIME?
MARY DONOHUE IS
AN ARCHITECTURAL HISTORIAN
WITH THE CONNECTICUT COMMISSION
ON CULTURE AND TOURISM.
HI, MARY, ELYSE.
HI.
LET'S HEAD IN HERE.
MARY, I'M INVESTIGATING
A FARMHOUSE IN CONNECTICUT
THAT DURING
THE EARLY 20th CENTURY
HAD A TREMENDOUS AMOUNT
OF TURNOVER WITH RUSSIAN JEWS,
AND I'M TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT WHY.
WELL, THEY SETTLED ON
THE LOWER EAST SIDE OF MANHATTAN
IN A VERY JEWISH AREA,
BUT THEN TO MOVE
TO THE COUNTRY
WAS A VERY HARD MOVE.
SUDDENLY, THEY'RE IN
THE CONNECTICUT COUNTRYSIDE,
WHERE THERE'S NOT A
READY-MADE JEWISH COMMUNITY,
THEY DIDN'T
SPEAK ENGLISH --
THAT MADE IT HARDER.
BUT MARY DOUBTS
RESENTMENT OF THE NEWCOMERS
WAS THE REASON
FOR THE HIGH TURNOVER.
I THINK IF
THE JEWISH FARMERS
WORKED HARD AND
BECAME SUCCESSFUL,
THEY REALLY HAD
THE YANKEE FARMERS' RESPECT.
BUT IF IT WASN'T
XENOPHOBIA,
WHY WEREN'T THE FAMILIES
WHO LIVED IN CHRIS'S FARMHOUSE
ABLE TO MAKE A GO
OF IT?
THE REAL BREAKTHROUGH
CAME THROUGH IN 1908.
WHAT MARY TELLS ME NEXT
PUTS ALL THE PIECES
OF THE PUZZLE IN PLACE.
IT'S TIME TO HEAD BACK
TO CHRIS.
CHRIS, I WASN'T ABLE TO FIND OUT
A LOT OF INFORMATION
ABOUT THE PEOPLE THAT
LIVED HERE,
BUT YOU WERE RIGHT,
THEY WERE RUSSIAN JEWS.
THAT'S GREAT.
PRETTY COOL, RIGHT?
PRETTY COOL.
I TELL CHRIS HOW,
WITH THE HELP OF ORGANIZATIONS
LIKE THE JEWISH
AGRICULTURAL SOCIETY,
IMMIGRANTS ESCAPED FROM
THE SLUMS OF NEW YORK CITY
TO FARMS SUCH AS HIS.
BUT WHEN THEY GOT HERE,
IT WAS A DIFFERENT STORY.
THEY REALLY DIDN'T HAVE
TRAINING AS FARMERS,
AND THESE ARE PEOPLE
THAT WERE REFUGEES.
THEY WERE IN THE TRADES,
THEY WERE PROFESSIONALS,
THEY WERE ALMOST ANYTHING
BUT A FARMER.
YOU WEREN'T EVEN ALLOWED
TO OWN LAND IN RUSSIA
IF YOU WERE JEWISH.
IT WAS ALSO
VERY MARGINAL LAND.
CONNECTICUT POTATOES
ARE REALLY ROCKS.
THIS IS FARMLAND THAT'S BEEN
USED HARD FOR OVER 200 YEARS.
MANY SIMPLY
COULDN'T MAKE IT,
AND THE OLD YANKEE FARMS
KEPT CHANGING HANDS.
WOW, THAT I WOULD NOT
HAVE GUESSED.
WELL, I GUESS THAT EXPLAINS
WHY THERE WAS SO MUCH TURNOVER.
THEY DIDN'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT THEY WERE DOING
AND DECIDED TO GIVE UP.
BUT THE STORY
DOESN'T END THERE.
MARY EXPLAINED THAT
THE ORGANIZATIONS
THAT HELPED
BUY THE FARMS
REALIZED THE EARLY IMMIGRANTS
NEEDED FURTHER ASSISTANCE.
THE REAL BREAKTHROUGH
CAME THROUGH IN 1908
WHEN THEY ALSO STARTED
TO PRODUCE A NEWSPAPER
IN YIDDISH FOR FARMERS
CALLED THE JEWISH FARMER,
WHICH WAS THE FIRST YIDDISH
AGRICULTURAL MAGAZINE
IN THE WORLD.
MARY'S FRIEND AVI
HAS AGREED TO HELP TRANSLATE
SOME OF THE YIDDISH.
ALL RIGHT,
HELP US OUT HERE.
AND THE FIRST ARTICLE
YOU HAVE
IS "HOW TO BEST UNDERSTAND
YOUR COW," OR...
[ speaks in Yiddish ]
AND THEN IT GOES ON
TO SAY IN YIDDISH
WHAT EVERY FARMER SHOULD
KNOW ABOUT THEIR COW.
[ speaking in Yiddish ]
"EVERY JEWISH FARMER
WHO HAS EYES HAS NOTICED
"THAT SOME COWS
GIVE MILK BETTER
AND SOME COWS
GIVE MILK WORSE."
WHAT YOU HAVE HERE IS THIS
HOW-TO GUIDE FOR JEWISH FARMERS,
EVERYTHING THEY NEED TO KNOW
HOW TO BE A FARMER,
ALL THE BASICS,
WRITTEN IN YIDDISH.
MARY, WITH ALL THIS INFORMATION
FROM THE JEWISH FARMER,
HOW DID THEY DO?
THEY DID GREAT.
IN 1908, IT ONLY HAD
638 SUBSCRIBERS,
AND FIVE YEARS LATER,
IT HAD THOUSANDS.
IN CONNECTICUT, JEWISH FARMERS
DEVELOPED A NICHE MARKET
FOR THINGS LIKE TOBACCO,
POULTRY, EGGS, DAIRY,
AND SECOND AND THIRD
GENERATION JEWISH FARMERS
REALLY PROSPERED.
YOU KNOW, SOME PEOPLE
DIDN'T MAKE IT
AND THEY WENT BACK
TO THE CITY,
BUT OTHER PEOPLE
WERE SMART
AND THEY FOUND OTHER WAYS
TO MAKE MONEY,
AND THEY TURNED THEIR FARMS
INTO EITHER BOARDING HOUSES
OR WEEKEND RESORTS,
SO MUCH SO,
THAT AT ONE TIME,
THIS AREA WAS CALLED
THE CATSKILLS OF NEW ENGLAND.
THE IDEA THAT THIS HOUSE
WAS MORE THAN A HOUSE,
THAT IT COULD HAVE BEEN
A SANCTUARY FOR PEOPLE,
I MEAN, THAT'S
JUST FANTASTIC.
WELL, IT WAS A GREAT EXPERIENCE,
AND THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
FOR MORE OF MY INTERVIEW
WITH DANIEL SAWYER,
VISIT HISTORY DETECTIVES
ON THE WEB AT pbs.org.
THE TOWN OF WILLIAMSBURG
IN BROOKLYN, NEW YORK,
ALSO SAW AN INFLUX
OF JEWISH RESIDENTS
AT THE TURN OF
THE 20th CENTURY
THANKS TO AN INCREDIBLE FEAT
OF AMERICAN ENGINEERING.
CONSTRUCTION ON
THE WILLIAMSBURG BRIDGE,
NEW YORK'S SECOND
GREAT SUSPENSION BRIDGE,
BEGAN ON
NOVEMBER 7th, 1896.
TO ALLEVIATE THE TRAFFIC
OVERWHELMING
THE BROOKLYN BRIDGE,
ITS DESIGN CALLED FOR
A DOUBLE-DECKER ROADWAY
FOR CARRIAGES, TROLLEYS,
AND PEDESTRIANS.
IN ORDER TO SUPPORT
TWO LEVELS OF TRAFFIC,
310-FOOT-HIGH TOWERS
WERE ERECTED,
THE FIRST EVER MADE
ENTIRELY OF STEEL.
BUILT IN HALF THE TIME
OF THE BROOKLYN BRIDGE
AND MEASURING FOUR AND A HALF
FEET LONGER,
THE WILLIAMSBURG BRIDGE
STOLE THE TITLE
OF THE LONGEST SUSPENSION
BRIDGE IN THE WORLD
WHEN IT OPENED ON
DECEMBER 19, 1903.
JEWISH RESIDENTS OF MANHATTAN'S
CROWDED EAST SIDE TENEMENTS
STREAMED OVER THIS
STATE-OF-THE-ART BRIDGE
TO FIND NEW HOMES
IN SPACIOUS BROOKLYN.
THE BRAND-NEW LINK
BETWEEN THE THEN-SEPARATE CITIES
OF NEW YORK AND BROOKLYN
ALSO PROVIDED
A FINAL IMPETUS
FOR THEM TO CONSOLIDATE.
IN 1898,
THEY JOINED WITH QUEENS,
STATEN ISLAND,
AND THE BRONX
TO BECOME THE SINGLE UNITED CITY
OF NEW YORK.
Tukufu:
OUR LAST STORY INVESTIGATES
THE CONNECTION
BETWEEN A PORTRAIT, A POET,
AND THE FALL OF AN EMPIRE.
IN 1923, THE LEBANESE-BORN
POET KHALIL GIBRAN
PUBLISHES THE PROPHET,
A COLLECTION OF POEMS
EXPLORING FACETS OF LIFE
AND THE HUMAN CONDITION.
ALTHOUGH VIEWED SKEPTICALLY
BY CRITICS,
IT WILL BECOME
A LITERARY SENSATION,
MAKING KHALIL GIBRAN ONE OF
THE WORLD'S BESTSELLING POETS
AND HAVING
A POWERFUL IMPACT
ON THE COUNTERCULTURE OF THE
1960s AND THE NEW-AGE MOVEMENT.
BUT MANY ARE UNAWARE
THAT THE WRITER
WAS ALSO
A PROLIFIC PAINTER,
CAPTURING CELEBRITIES
AND FAMOUS FIGURES
OF THE 20th CENTURY
ON CANVAS.
NOW, ALMOST EIGHT DECADES
AFTER GIBRAN'S DEATH,
BOB DIAB FROM OVERLAND PARK,
KANSAS, HAS A PORTRAIT
THAT HE THINKS MAY HAVE BEEN
PAINTED BY GIBRAN.
[ doorbell rings ]
HELLO, I'M TUKUFU.
I'M BOB.
PLEASE COME IN.
WOW, SO WHAT IS THIS?
THIS IS MY GRANDFATHER,
NAJEEB MUSA DIAB.
HE WAS A PUBLISHER
OF AN ARABIC NEWSPAPER
IN BROOKLYN, NEW YORK,
AT THE TURN OF THE CENTURY.
JUST AFTER HE IMMIGRATED HERE
FROM SYRIA.
AND WHICH PAPER
WAS THAT?
IT WAS CALLED
THE MIRROR OF THE WEST.
BOB SAYS HIS
GRANDFATHER'S NEWSPAPER
WAS ONCE AN IMPORTANT RESOURCE
FOR ARAB IMMIGRANTS,
A FAMILIAR VOICE
REPORTING ON CHANGING EVENTS
IN THEIR HOME COUNTRIES
AND ON LIFE WITHIN
ARAB IMMIGRANT COMMUNITIES
IN THE UNITED STATES.
HE PUBLISHED GIBRAN'S POEMS
IN HIS NEWSPAPER,
GIVING THE POET
A PROMINENT VOICE
IN THE ISOLATED
ARAB COMMUNITY.
WHAT IS IT ABOUT THIS PAINTING
THAT'S SO IMPORTANT?
THE STORY IS THAT IT
WAS PAINTED BY KHALIL GIBRAN.
NOW, I KNOW OF HIM
AS A VERY FAMOUS WRITER,
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW
HE DID PAINTINGS.
YES.
ESPECIALLY PORTRAITS.
AND I KNOW THAT HE...
BOB TELLS ME A COUSIN
HE HASN'T SEEN IN MANY YEARS
ONCE HAD A DRAWING
SIGNED BY THE POET.
ALTHOUGH THE PAINTING
OF BOB'S GRANDFATHER
IS NOT SIGNED, THERE ARE
SOME POTENTIAL CLUES.
WHAT IS THIS MEDAL HERE,
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT'S ABOUT?
I DO NOT KNOW.
AND THIS HERE,
THIS IS A WATCH, RIGHT?
BOB HAS A TIMEPIECE
THAT HAS BEEN PASSED DOWN
THROUGH HIS FAMILY
WHICH HE THINKS MAY BE
THE SAME WATCH
IN THE PAINTING.
THIS POCKET WATCH WAS
PRESENTED TO MY GRANDFATHER
WHEN HE WAS PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED SYRIAN SOCIETY
IN 1914 TO 1915.
FINE TIMEPIECE.
THANK YOU.
BOB SAYS THAT ALTHOUGH
HIS GRANDFATHER
IMMIGRATED TO
THE UNITED STATES,
HE DEVOTED HIS LIFE
TO THE CAUSE OF INDEPENDENCE
FOR SYRIA AND LEBANON.
BOTH WERE STILL PART
OF THE OTTOMAN EMPIRE,
WHICH HAD RULED THOSE LANDS
FOR SEVERAL HUNDRED YEARS.
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO FIND OUT FOR YOU?
WELL, COULD IT HAVE BEEN
PAINTED BY KHALIL GIBRAN
AND ANY BACKGROUND
ABOUT MY GRANDFATHER.
THE PORTRAIT IS TOO LARGE
TO CARRY WITH ME,
SO I'M GOING TO TAKE
SOME PHOTOS.
I READ KHALIL GIBRAN
IN COLLEGE,
BUT I DON'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT HIS ARTWORK.
I'M HEADING INTO BROOKLYN,
NEW YORK, HOME TO A LARGE
AND LONG-STANDING
ARAB-AMERICAN COMMUNITY,
TO SHOW BOB'S PAINTING
TO A KHALIL GIBRAN SCHOLAR,
GREGORY ORFALEA.
WELCOME.
GREG SAYS MUCH OF GIBRAN'S
WRITING AND PAINTING
REFLECTS HIS IDENTITY
AS AN IMMIGRANT
IN A FOREIGN LAND.
I THINK HIS EXPERIENCE
IN AMERICA
WAS ONE OF ALIENATION.
IT WAS A LONELY EXPERIENCE
LINGUISTICALLY.
HE DIDN'T KNOW ENGLISH.
HE WAS NOT IN BEAUTIFUL,
VERDANT, SNOWY MT. LEBANON,
HE WAS LIVING IN THE TENEMENTS
IN GRIMY BOSTON,
SOUTH BOSTON,
WEST ROXBURY.
GREG EXPLAINS THAT GIBRAN
ARRIVED IN BOSTON IN 1895
AT THE AGE OF 12.
HIS FAMILY WAS PART
OF AN ENORMOUS INFLUX
OF MOSTLY POOR IMMIGRANTS
WHO ARRIVED
AT THE TURN OF THE CENTURY
FROM LEBANON AND SYRIA
TO PLACES SUCH AS
BROOKLYN, NEW YORK,
AND SOUTH BOSTON.
HIS FIRST POETRY
WAS IN ARABIC
AND OFTEN ADDRESSED YOUNG
IMMIGRANTS LIKE HIMSELF
STRUGGLING TO FIND THEIR WAY
IN THE UNITED STATES.
HE WROTE POEMS
TO TELL YOUNG SYRIAN AMERICANS
TO BE PROUD OF THEIR HERITAGE
IN THE UNITED STATES
AND FEEL THAT THEY HAD
SOMETHING TO GIVE OF MAGNITUDE.
IN 1923, HE PUBLISHED
A COLLECTION
OF 26 ENGLISH PROSE POEMS
ABOUT A MYSTICAL SPIRITUAL
LEADER, THE PROPHET.
IN IT, GIBRAN EXPLORED SUBJECTS
LIKE LOVE, BEAUTY, AND GIVING.
"YOU GIVE BUT LITTLE WHEN
YOU GIVE OF YOUR POSSESSIONS.
IT IS WHEN YOU GIVE OF YOURSELF
THAT YOU TRULY GIVE."
THE UNIQUE BLEND OF EAST
AND WEST THINKING
HAS SOLD MILLIONS
OF COPIES.
THERE ARE SOME PARTS
OF THE PROPHET
THAT ARE VERY INTERESTING,
AND SOME OF THE APHORISMS
THAT ARE DIFFERENT.
"WORK IS LOVE MADE VISIBLE."
IT WAS A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
STYLE OF WRITING
THAN WAS GOING ON RIGHT THEN
AND THERE WITH THE AMERICANS.
BUT GREG BELIEVES THAT,
IRONICALLY,
THE PROPHET'S COMMERCIAL
SUCCESS MAY HAVE CONTRIBUTED
TO GIBRAN'S MIXED REVIEWS
FROM CRITICS.
AND ALSO YOU HAVE TO SAY
THAT ANOTHER REASON WAS
THAT THEY JUST SIMPLY
DID NOT TRANSLATE
HIS TOUGHER, MORE REBELLIOUS,
PRINCIPLED POLITICAL WORK
THAT WAS PUBLISHED
PRIOR TO THE PROPHET.
WE TRANSLATED A POEM OF HIS
THAT HAD NEVER SEEN ENGLISH,
"DEFEAT, MY DEFEAT."
THAT MATERIAL SHOWS
A MORE POLITICAL,
MORE DEFIANT,
MORE SOCIALLY ENGAGED GIBRAN.
I'LL READ JUST A BIT
OF IT.
"DEFEAT, MY DEFEAT,
MY SHINING SWORD AND SHIELD.
"IN YOUR EYES I HAVE READ
"THAT TO BE ENTHRONED
IS TO BE ENSLAVED,
"AND WE SHALL STAND
IN THE SUN WITH A WILL
AND WE SHALL BE DANGEROUS."
SALMA JAYYUSI,
THE PALESTINIAN CRITIC,
SAYS THAT HE IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT LITERARY FIGURE
IN THE ARAB WORLD IN THE FIRST
HALF OF THE 20th CENTURY.
THAT'S BIG.
I TELL GREG ABOUT
MY INVESTIGATION.
SO I'M PARTICULARLY INTERESTED
IN THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN KHALIL GIBRAN
AND NAJEEB DIAB.
CAN YOU TALK TO ME
A LITTLE BIT ABOUT DIAB?
WELL, HE WAS A LEADER OF
THE COMMUNITY AS A JOURNALIST.
HE WAS A LEADER OF
THE UNITED SYRIAN SOCIETY.
IT WAS FOR FREEDOM
FOR SYRIA FROM OTTOMAN TURKEY.
HE WAS
A HIGHLY RESPECTED MAN.
GREG CONFIRMS BOTH MEN
KNEW EACH OTHER
AND MOVED
IN SIMILAR CIRCLES,
EACH SPEAKING IN FAVOR
OF INDEPENDENCE
FOR SYRIA AND LEBANON.
LIKE GIBRAN, NAJEEB DIAB
WAS PROFOUNDLY INFLUENCED
BY AMERICAN IDEAS OF POLITICAL
LIBERTY AND FREE SPEECH.
THESE PEOPLE HAD
COME TO AMERICA,
THEY HAD TASTED THE FRUITS
OF DEMOCRACY AND SECULARISM.
MOST OF THEM LIKED
WHAT THEY SAW
AND LIKED WHAT THEY TASTED.
THEY WANTED TO SEE IT
IN THEIR HOME COUNTRIES.
BUT GREG'S NOT SURE
IF GIBRAN EVER PAINTED THIS.
IT'S ALMOST TOO REALISTIC.
THERE'S NO PRE-RAPHAELITE LIGHT
AND MISTINESS ABOUT IT
THAT YOU SAW
IN GIBRAN'S PAINTINGS.
HE SAYS THE LARGEST
PUBLIC COLLECTION
OF GIBRAN PAINTINGS
IN THE U.S.
IS AT THE TELFAIR MUSEUM
IN SAVANNAH, GEORGIA,
SO I'M ARRANGING
TO HAVE BOB'S PORTRAIT
SHIPPED THERE
FOR COMPARISON.
MEANWHILE, I'M GOING TO TRY
TO TRACK DOWN BOB'S COUSIN,
WHOM HE HAD SAID ONCE OWNED
ARTWORK SIGNED BY GIBRAN.
EVENTUALLY, I LOCATE
ROBERT MADEY
ON LONG ISLAND
NEAR NEW YORK CITY.
ROBERT IS ALSO A GRANDSON
OF THE MAN IN BOB'S PORTRAIT,
NAJEEB DIAB.
WELCOME.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
NOW, IT'S MY UNDERSTANDING
THAT YOU ACTUALLY HAVE A SKETCH
THAT KHALIL GIBRAN
DID AND SIGNED.
I DO, AND AS
A MATTER OF FACT...
ROBERT SHOWS ME
THE SKETCH OF HIS AUNT SELMA.
THE WOMAN IS NAJEEB DIAB'S
DAUGHTER.
HE SAYS THAT ALTHOUGH
THE ORIGINAL HAS BEEN SOLD,
THERE'S NO DOUBT
WHO DREW IT.
"MY LOVE TO SELMA DIAB
FROM GIBRAN GIBRAN."
WOW, VERY,
VERY INTERESTING.
WELL, GIBRAN AND MY GRANDFATHER
WERE FRIENDS.
ROBERT EXPLAINS
THAT KHALIL GIBRAN
WAS CLOSE TO HIS
ENTIRE FAMILY,
SHARING POLITICAL
AND ARTISTIC INTERESTS.
THEY WERE FOUNDERS OF A SOCIETY
CALLED AL-RABITAH,
AND THAT ORGANIZATION
WAS FORMED TO PROMOTE
AND PERPETUATE THE
ARABIC LANGUAGE AND CULTURE
AND LITERATURE
IN THIS COUNTRY.
AND MY FATHER, IN FACT,
DELIVERED A EULOGY TO GIBRAN
WHEN HE PASSED AWAY.
I'M DOING AN INVESTIGATION
TO FIND OUT
IF KHALIL GIBRAN COULD HAVE
ACTUALLY PAINTED THIS PORTRAIT.
HAVE YOU EVER
SEEN THIS BEFORE?
I HAVE.
I HAVE THE ORIGINAL PHOTO
FROM WHICH THIS PORTRAIT
WAS PAINTED.
THIS IS AMAZING.
THE TWIST IN THE HAIR
IS AT THE EXACT SAME PLACE,
THE TIE IS THE SAME,
THE COAT IS THE SAME,
THE NUMBER OF BUTTONS
ARE THE SAME.
DO YOU KNOW WHEN
THIS PHOTOGRAPH WAS TAKEN?
NO, BUT I THINK IT WAS DONE
PROBABLY IN CONNECTION
WITH A CONFERENCE HE ATTENDED
IN PARIS IN 1913.
IT MAY HAVE BEEN DONE JUST
PRIOR TO OR JUST AFTERWARDS.
ROBERT SAYS HIS GRANDFATHER
ATTENDED
A MAJOR CONFERENCE IN PARIS
JUST BEFORE WORLD WAR I
AS THE HEAD OF
THE UNITED SYRIAN SOCIETY.
DELEGATES FROM ARAB NATIONS
AND OTHER IMMIGRANT GROUPS
WERE DEBATING THE BEST WAY
OF ENDING TURKISH RULE
IN SYRIA AND LEBANON.
THE WATCH BOB SHOWED ME
WAS ALSO FROM
THE UNITED SYRIAN SOCIETY
AND MAY WELL BE THE SAME WATCH
IN THE PORTRAIT.
HAD GIBRAN PAINTED
THIS IMAGE OF HIS FRIEND
TO COMMEMORATE
THIS IMPORTANT MOMENT?
BOB'S SKEPTICAL THE PAINTING
WAS DONE BY GIBRAN --
THE STYLE IS SO DIFFERENT
FROM THE IMAGE OF HIS AUNT --
BUT HE CAN'T BE CERTAIN.
IT'S CONCEIVABLE THAT
HE COULD'VE DONE A COPY.
BOB'S PAINTING HAS ARRIVED
AT THE TELFAIR MUSEUM,
WHERE I'M MEETING CURATOR
TANIA SAMMONS.
WE ARE TRYING TO FIND OUT
IF THIS PAINTING
WAS DONE BY GIBRAN.
WELL, KHALIL GIBRAN ACTUALLY WAS
FIRST KNOWN FOR HIS ARTWORK.
TANIA TELLS ME
THAT GIBRAN'S TALENT
WON THE ATTENTION
OF BOSTON'S ART COMMUNITY
WHILE HE WAS STILL
A TEEN.
A SCHOOL HEADMISTRESS
NAMED MARY HASKELL
BECAME HIS PATRON
AND EVENTUALLY HIS LOVER.
SHE SENT HIM TO STUDY ART
AT THE ACADEMIE JULIAN IN PARIS
AND HAD A PROFOUND INFLUENCE
ON HIS LIFE.
IN 1911, SHE HELPED HIM SET UP
A STUDIO IN NEW YORK CITY.
SHE REALLY ALLOWED HIM
TO TAKE OFF,
BOTH IN HIS WRITING
AND VISUAL CAREERS.
SO NOT ONLY DID SHE ENCOURAGE
HIM TO WRITE IN ENGLISH,
BUT SHE HELPED HIM
LEARN THE LANGUAGE,
SHE EDITED HIS WORK
AS WELL.
NOW, DOES THE LACK OF
A SIGNATURE TELL US ANYTHING?
KHALIL GIBRAN
DID SIGN HIS PIECES,
BUT HE DIDN'T
SIGN EVERYTHING.
HOWEVER, I WOULD SAY
THE STYLE OF PAINTING
IS NOT TYPICAL
FOR KHALIL GIBRAN.
TANIA SHOWS ME A SERIES
OF PAINTINGS BY GIBRAN,
AND AT FIRST GLIMPSE,
HIS WORKS DO NOT RESEMBLE
THE DIAB PORTRAIT.
YOU CAN SEE HOW HE IS
NOT REALLY FOCUSED
ON THE INDIVIDUAL FEATURES
OF A PERSON.
IT'S VERY FLUID.
YEAH.
DO YOU HAVE ANY OIL PAINTINGS
LIKE OURS WHICH ARE A PORTRAIT?
I HAVE A GOOD COMPARISON.
IT'S A SELF-PORTRAIT
OF KHALIL GIBRAN.
THE STYLE OF THIS PORTRAIT
IS ALSO QUITE DIFFERENT
FROM BOB'S.
IN THIS PAINTING,
GIBRAN'S BRUSH STROKES
ARE VERY EVIDENT.
THEY'RE MUCH FREER.
YOU CAN SEE INDIVIDUAL COLORS
IN THE PAINTING
AND HIS FACE
ISN'T DELINEATED
LIKE THE IMAGE
OF MR. DIAB.
I EXPLAIN THAT BOB'S PORTRAIT
MAY HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH NAJEEB DIAB ATTENDING
A MAJOR CONFERENCE
IN PARIS IN 1913.
TANIA SAYS THAT
DURING THAT PERIOD,
GIBRAN DID A NUMBER
OF PAINTINGS AND DRAWINGS
OF IMPORTANT ARTISTS
AND THINKERS.
HE CALLED IT
THE "TEMPLE OF ART" SERIES.
CERTAINLY MR. DIAB WOULD HAVE
FIT WITHIN THAT SERIES.
AND SO IT WOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN
UNCALLED FOR
FOR DIAB TO REQUEST
A PARTICULAR TYPE OF PORTRAIT
FROM GIBRAN.
YEAH, CERTAINLY NOT.
IT'S TYPICAL FOR PEOPLE
WHO COMMISSION PORTRAITS
TO GUIDE THE ARTIST
ON HOW THEY WOULD LIKE
FOR THE PORTRAIT
TO BE PAINTED.
DOES BOB HAVE A PREVIOUSLY
UNKNOWN PAINTING
FROM THE
"TEMPLE OF ART" SERIES?
TANIA SUGGESTS THAT IF DIAB
HAD COMMISSIONED THE WORK,
GIBRAN MAY HAVE MENTIONED IT
IN HIS CORRESPONDENCE
WITH HIS LOVER,
MARY HASKELL.
LET ME SEE
IF I CAN FIND ANYTHING
ABOUT THE
"TEMPLE OF ART" HERE.
THERE ARE REFERENCES
TO MANY OF THE LUMINARIES
THAT GIBRAN DREW
OR PAINTED,
INCLUDING PSYCHOTHERAPIST
CARL JUNG,
IRISH POET
WILLIAM BUTLER YEATS,
AND THE LEGENDARY ACTRESS
SARAH BERNHARDT.
LISTEN TO THIS:
"AT LAST, THE DIVINE
SARAH IS CAUGHT."
THIS IS A REFERENCE
TO SARAH BERNHARDT.
"BUT IF I AM TO GO
THROUGH THE SAME PROCESS
"WITH OTHER GREAT MEN
AND WOMEN,
"I MIGHT AS WELL GIVE UP ART
AND BECOME A DIPLOMAT."
OKAY, HERE IS A REFERENCE
TO DIAB.
I'VE DISCOVERED
A CURIOUS NOTE
IN THE HASKELL LETTERS.
I THINK I FINALLY HAVE
SOME ANSWERS FOR BOB.
BOB, THIS INVESTIGATION
HAS ALLOWED US
TO GAIN SOME INSIGHT
OF THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN YOUR GRANDFATHER
AND KHALIL GIBRAN.
I SPOKE TO AN EXPERT
ON HIS ARTWORK,
AND SHE IS OF THE OPINION
THAT THIS PAINTING
IS NOT THE WORK
OF KHALIL GIBRAN.
I EXPLAIN TO BOB
THAT TO MAKE CERTAIN,
I CONSULTED THE LETTERS
AND DIARIES OF MARY HASKELL.
AND IT IS THAT SEARCH
WHICH LED ME
TO ONE OF MY MOST
IMPORTANT DISCOVERIES.
OKAY, HERE IS A REFERENCE
TO DIAB.
IT'S QUITE POLITICAL,
AND THIS IS REFERRING
TO THE 1913 PARIS
CONFERENCE.
"DIAB AND MYSELF WERE ASKED
TO GO AS REPRESENTATIVES.
"THE IDEA IS FINE,
BUT AFTER TALKING THINGS OVER
"WITH A COMMITTEE
OF SYRIANS,
"I FOUND THAT WE
DO NOT AGREE ON ANY POINT.
"DIAB THINKS I AM MAD --
OTHERS THINK SO, TOO."
IT HAS NOTHING TO SAY
ABOUT HIM DOING A SKETCH
OR A PORTRAIT OF DIAB.
I TELL BOB THAT GIBRAN
HAD REFUSED TO ATTEND
THE 1913 PARIS CONFERENCE
BECAUSE HE HAD
FUNDAMENTAL DIFFERENCES
WITH OTHER ATTENDEES,
INCLUDING NAJEEB DIAB.
SO IT SEEMS UNLIKELY
THAT GIBRAN WOULD
PAINT A PORTRAIT
IN COMMEMORATION
OF THE EVENT.
THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN
YOUR GRANDFATHER
AND KHALIL GIBRAN
WAS NOT ONLY OVER ISSUES
OF WRITING AND ART,
IT WENT TO THE HEART
OF THEIR POLITICAL COMMITMENT
AND WAS A REFLECTION
ON THE EARLY ARAB-AMERICAN
POLITICAL LEADERSHIP
IN THIS COUNTRY.
IT'S QUITE INTERESTING.
I NEVER REALIZED THAT
THEY WERE EVEN IN POLITICS,
MY GRANDFATHER
OR KHALIL GIBRAN.
IT'S THE ONLY PICTURE
I HAVE OF MY GRANDFATHER,
AND I'LL STILL KEEP IT
AND CHERISH IT AT HOME.
I THANK YOU.
IN THE 1960s,
A GENERATION HUNGRY FOR CHANGE
WAS CAPTIVATED
BY PASSAGES FROM THE PROPHET,
LIKE "LOVE POSSESSES NOT
NOR WOULD IT BE POSSESSED;
FOR LOVE IS SUFFICIENT
UNTO LOVE."
IN THEIR SEARCH FOR A DIFFERENT
WAY OF THINKING AND LIVING,
MANY YOUNG, DISILLUSIONED
AMERICANS
TURNED TO THE TEACHINGS
OF THE EAST.
THE IDEAS EXPRESSED
IN THE PROPHET
MIRRORED THEIR STRUGGLE OF
THE SPIRIT AGAINST MATERIALISM.
KHALIL GIBRAN
BECAME A VOICE
FOR THE
COUNTERCULTURE MOVEMENT.
BUT GIBRAN
NEVER LIVED
TO SEE HIS WORDS INSPIRE
THAT GENERATION OF AMERICANS.
HE DIED OF CIRRHOSIS
OF THE LIVER
FROM ALCOHOLISM
IN 1931.
And so, my fellow Americans...
Elyse:
PRESIDENT KENNEDY IS
BELIEVED TO HAVE PARAPHRASED
KHALIL GIBRAN'S WRITING
WHEN HE SAID:
Ask not what your country
can do for you,
ask what you can do
for your country.
[ cheering and applause ]
JFK WAS ALSO FOND
OF QUOTING FROM ROBERT FROST
AND EVEN HAD THE POET READ
AT HIS INAUGURATION.
IT'S RARE THAT POETRY
AND POLITICS MIX,
BUT SOMETIMES TRAGEDY
BRINGS THE TWO TOGETHER.
FOLLOWING THE DISASTER
THAT CLAIMED THE LIVES
OF SEVEN ASTRONAUTS ABOARD
THE SPACE SHUTTLE CHALLENGER
ON JANUARY 28, 1986, RONALD
REAGAN ADDRESSED THE NATION.
We will never forget them.
WHEN HE ENDED HIS REMARKS
BY SAYING THE ASTRONAUTS HAD...
Slipped the surly bonds of
Earth to touch the face of God.
HE WAS BORROWING
FROM THE FIRST AND LAST LINE
OF "HIGH FLIGHT."
THE POEM WAS WRITTEN
IN 1941
BY A 19-YEAR-OLD PILOT
OFFICER,
JOHN GILLESPIE MAGEE, JR.,
ON THE BACK OF A LETTER
TO HIS MOTHER
JUST A FEW MONTHS
BEFORE HE WAS KILLED.
WHEN MARTIN LUTHER KING, JR.,
WAS ASSASSINATED,
BOBBY KENNEDY WENT BACK
2,500 YEARS
TO THE GREEK POET
AESCHYLUS
TO GIVE VOICE
TO HIS HOPE FOR THE FUTURE.
Kennedy:
Even in our sleep,
pain which cannot forget
falls drop by drop
upon the heart
until in our own despair,
against our will,
comes wisdom
through the awful grace of God.
Tukufu:
BE A HISTORY DETECTIVE
YOURSELF.
GO TO pbs.org
AND LEARN MORE ABOUT
INVESTIGATIVE TECHNIQUES
OR SUBMIT YOUR OWN MYSTERY
TO THE TEAM.
YOU CAN ALSO FIND OUT MORE
ABOUT TONIGHT'S INVESTIGATIONS
ONLY AT pbs.org.
THIS EPISODE OF HISTORY
DETECTIVES IS AVAILABLE ON DVD.
THE COMPANION BOOK TO
THE PROGRAM IS ALSO AVAILABLE.
TO ORDER,
CALL PBS HOME VIDEO AT...
OR VISIT US ONLINE AT...
Captions by LNS Captioning
Portland, Oregon
www.LNScaptioning.com
Elvis Costello:
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ IT'S JUST LIKE
WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
Gwendolyn:
THIS PROGRAM WAS MADE POSSIBLE
BY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO YOUR PBS STATION
FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.
WE'RE THE HISTORY DETECTIVES,
AND WE'RE GOING TO INVESTIGATE
SOME UNTOLD STORIES
FROM AMERICA'S PAST.