Elyse:
WE'RE THE HISTORY DETECTIVES,
AND WE'RE GOING TO INVESTIGATE
SOME UNTOLD STORIES
FROM AMERICA'S PAST.
Gwendolyn:
THIS WEEK...
She has already been taken
into custody by the FBI.
WHAT EVIDENCE FROM
THE TREASON TRIAL OF TOKYO ROSE
COULD THIS ODD DISC HOLD?
IT BECAME A COVER-UP.
Elyse:
IS THIS THE HOLY GRAIL
OF THE WILD WEST?
A PHOTOGRAPH OF THE LEGENDARY
WARRIOR CRAZY HORSE.
NOBODY HAS EVER PRODUCED A
PHOTOGRAPH OF CRAZY HORSE, EVER.
Wes:
AND IN AN ENCORE PRESENTATION,
DOES THIS DIARY HOLD THE KEY
TO UNDERSTANDING THE FATE
OF A MISSING BOMBER PILOT
FROM WORLD WAR II?
Elvis Costello:
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ I GET SO ANGRY
WHEN THE TEARDROPS START ♪
♪ BUT HE CAN'T BE WOUNDED
'CAUSE HE'S GOT NO HEART ♪
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ IT'S JUST LIKE
WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
Gwendolyn:
THIS PROGRAM WAS MADE POSSIBLE
BY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO YOUR PBS STATION
FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.
OUR FIRST STORY EXPLORES
WHETHER THIS 1940s RECORDING
MAY HAVE HELPED CONVICT
THE WOMAN ALLEGED TO BE
TOKYO ROSE.
WORLD WAR II,
THE LONELY PACIFIC:
AS MANY AS 2 MILLION SERVICEMEN
LISTEN WISTFULLY
WHILE A WOMAN'S VOICE
FLOATS OVER THE AIRWAVES.
Greetings, everybody.
This is your number-one enemy,
your favorite playmate...
THEY CALL HER
TOKYO ROSE.
MANY G.I.s CONSIDERED HER
A GODSEND,
A FAMILIAR AMERICAN VOICE
KEEPING THEM COMPANY
FAR FROM HOME.
BUT IN A CELEBRATED
POSTWAR TRIAL,
PROSECUTORS PORTRAYED HER
AS AN AMERICAN DEVIL,
A SIREN WHO KNOWINGLY WORKED
FOR THE ENEMY,
LURING SOLDIERS AND SAILORS,
THEN UNDERMINING
THEIR FIGHTING SPIRIT.
IN 1948, THE WOMAN
WHO TWICE SIGNED HER NAME
"THE ONE AND ORIGINAL
TOKYO ROSE"
WAS BROUGHT BACK FROM JAPAN
TO FACE A GRAND JURY.
THE WAR HAD ENDED,
BUT HER BATTLE HAD JUST BEGUN.
NOW BILL MOORE
FROM SUN CITY WEST, ARIZONA,
HAS AN OBJECT THAT MAY EXPLAIN
THE STORY BEHIND
HER CONFESSION.
MY UNCLE WENT TO JAPAN
TO GET TOKYO ROSE.
HI, YOU'RE BILL?
SO I HEAR YOU HAVE
A RECORD TO SHOW ME.
IS THIS IT?
YES, THIS IS IT.
WOW, IT'S UNUSUAL.
THIS MUST BE 16 INCHES ACROSS.
SIXTEEN INCHES, I THINK.
SOMEONE'S WRITTEN "TOKYO ROSE"
ON THE RECORD.
BILL FOUND IT WITH HIS MOTHER'S
THINGS AFTER SHE PASSED AWAY,
BUT HE BELIEVES
IT ORIGINALLY BELONGED
TO HIS LARGER-THAN-LIFE UNCLE,
HARRY BRUNDIDGE.
THIS IS MY UNCLE HARRY
AND MY AUNT JANET.
WHAT DID HE DO?
WELL, HE WAS
A WAR CORRESPONDENT
AND ASSOCIATE EDITOR
OF COSMOPOLITAN MAGAZINE.
THIS IS YOU, IS THAT RIGHT?
OH, YEAH.
SO WERE YOU OUT
IN THE PACIFIC?
TWO YEARS,
AND WE USED TO LISTEN
TO TOKYO ROSE ALL THE TIME.
BILL HAD HEARD THAT HIS UNCLE
MET TOKYO ROSE ON ASSIGNMENT
AND BELIEVES HE PLAYED
A KEY ROLE IN HER PROSECUTION.
AFTER THE WAR,
HE WENT BACK OVER TO JAPAN
AND HE GOT TOKYO ROSE,
BROUGHT HER BACK
TO SAN FRANCISCO,
AND HAD HER INDICTED
FOR TREASON.
BILL THINKS THE RECORD
MAY HAVE BEEN USED
AS EVIDENCE
IN HER TRIAL,
BUT HE'S NEVER BEEN ABLE
TO HEAR WHAT'S ON THE RECORDING
BECAUSE IT'S TOO LARGE
TO PLAY ON STANDARD EQUIPMENT.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT -- OF COURSE,
WHAT I HEARD FROM MY FAMILY,
THAT THIS WAS
PART OF THE TRIAL.
WHAT EXACTLY WOULD YOU LIKE
FOR ME TO FIND OUT
ABOUT YOUR RECORD?
I'D LIKE TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S ON IT, OF COURSE,
AND ABOUT MY UNCLE
IN THE TRIAL.
I'LL HAVE TO TAKE THIS
WITH ME, AND I'D LIKE TO TAKE
THE PHOTOGRAPHS, TOO,
IF THAT'S OKAY.
OH, YOU CAN, YEAH.
I FOUND A STUDIO
WITH A TURNTABLE
THAT CAN PLAY
THE OVERSIZED DISC.
I'M IN LONG ISLAND CITY,
NEW YORK,
TO MEET AUDIO ENGINEER
GUY ROSMARIN AT VIDIPAX.
OOH, WOW, I HAVEN'T SEEN
ONE OF THESE IN A WHILE.
WHAT IS IT MADE OF?
PROBABLY ALUMINUM-BASED.
THEY STARTED USING IT AGAIN
AFTER THE WAR.
YOU COULDN'T USE ALUMINUM
DURING THE WAR
FOR ANYTHING EXCEPT WAR.
THAT'S RIGHT.
Female Voice:
All right, take it now
from five.
Tokyo Rose will touch
American soil in a few moments
and will immediately be taken
into custody.
WELL, THIS CERTAINLY DOESN'T
SOUND LIKE COURTROOM EVIDENCE,
BUT BILL'S UNCLE IS DEFINITELY
PART OF THE ACTION.
We're fortunate today in having
two very famous correspondents.
Harry Brundidge...
GUY HAS MADE A CD COPY FOR ME.
BILL'S UNCLE HARRY
IS SPEAKING NOW.
She just shook hands with me
as she came off the boat
and recognized me.
Female Voice:
I noticed that.
IVA TOGURI, THE WOMAN
WHO WAS TRIED AS TOKYO ROSE,
WAS BORN IN LOS ANGELES
TO FIRST-GENERATION
JAPANESE IMMIGRANTS.
SHE LEFT THE U.S.
IN THE SUMMER OF '41
TO CARE FOR A SICK AUNT
IN TOKYO.
AFTER PEARL HARBOR,
WARTIME BUREAUCRACY
MADE IT IMPOSSIBLE FOR HER
TO RETURN TO THE U.S.
STRANDED IN JAPAN
DURING THE WAR,
IVA FOUND A JOB
AT RADIO TOKYO AS A TYPIST
UNTIL SHE WAS TAPPED
TO HOST
A JAPANESE WAR
PROPAGANDA PROGRAM.
IVA'S BROADCASTS WOULD BE
AT THE CENTER OF WHAT WAS THEN
ONE OF THE COSTLIEST TRIALS
IN U.S. HISTORY.
THAT TRIAL COST
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT $750,000.
IN TODAY'S MONEY
THAT'S ALMOST $7 MILLION.
OF THE EIGHT COUNTS
BROUGHT AGAINST HER,
THE GRAND JURY FOUND HER GUILTY
OF ONLY ONE,
ANNOUNCING THE LOSS
OF AMERICAN SHIPS.
I'M IN NEW YORK CITY,
MEETING WITH MEDIA HISTORIAN
STEVEN PHIPPS.
I'M EAGER FOR YOU
TO HEAR THIS.
Female Voice:
There are crowds here
that have been standing
since 9:00 this morning
waiting to see Tokyo Rose,
the girl who undermined
the morale -- or tried to --
of our boys
in the Pacific.
WELL, THIS IS OBVIOUSLY
A NEWS REPORT,
AND IT'S CLEAR THAT IT MUST
HAVE BEEN SEPTEMBER 25, 1948.
STEVEN SAYS THAT'S WHEN IVA
RETURNED TO THE UNITED STATES
BY MILITARY ESCORT.
THE PRESS AND PUBLIC CLAMORED
FOR A CLOSER LOOK
AT THE WOMAN THE MEDIA
HAD ALREADY BRANDED
A WARTIME TRAITOR:
TOKYO ROSE.
BUT THERE WAS NO EVIDENCE
THAT SHE WAS THE TOKYO ROSE.
IN FACT, THERE WAS NO ONE PERSON
WHO WAS THE TOKYO ROSE.
AS BILL TOLD ME EARLIER,
THE G.I.s USED THAT NAME
FOR ALL THE ENGLISH-SPEAKING
FEMALE HOSTS
BROADCASTING IN THE PACIFIC.
THE JAPANESE FELT THAT
USING A WOMAN ANNOUNCER
WOULD MAKE THE G.I.s
MORE PRONE TO LISTEN
AND THAT IT WOULD TEND
TO MAKE THEM HOMESICK.
WHY DID BRUNDIDGE CLAIM
IVA WAS TOKYO ROSE?
STEVEN HAS DONE SOME DIGGING
ON THE REPORTER'S BACKGROUND.
I FOUND QUITE A FEW ARTICLES
ON BRUNDIDGE,
SINCE I KNOW THAT
YOU'RE INTERESTED IN HIM.
MUCH OF HIS EARLY CAREER
WAS IN ST. LOUIS,
REPORTING ON THE MOB.
STEVEN DISCOVERED BRUNDIDGE
HAD A FLAIR FOR THE DRAMATIC
AND OFTEN PLAYED FAST AND LOOSE
WITH THE FACTS.
HERE'S ONE FROM 1930.
THIS ONE IS CALLED
"CALL BRUNDIDGE STORY HEARSAY."
SO FOR YEARS HE'D
BEEN KNOWN AS SOMEONE
WHO WAS PUSHING
THE TRUTH ON HIS STORIES.
WELL, YES.
WHAT WAS HIS INVOLVEMENT
IN THE TOKYO ROSE STORY?
LET ME SHOW YOU
IN THIS ARTICLE.
IT'S A MAY 1948
FRONT-PAGE STORY
FROM THE NASHVILLE TENNESSEAN.
THAT'S FOUR MONTHS BEFORE
THE DATE ON OUR RECORDING.
IN IT, BRUNDIDGE DETAILS
HIS TIME IN JAPAN
HUNTING FOR EMPEROR HIROHITO,
THEN FOR TOKYO ROSE.
IN HIS STORY, BRUNDIDGE TAKES
CREDIT FOR HER INDICTMENT.
THERE'S A REFERENCE
TO SECRET WITNESSES
THAT BRUNDIDGE CAME UP WITH.
BUT DO WE KNOW
WHO THEY WERE?
I HAVE NO CLUE.
STEVEN GIVES ME THE NAME
OF A JOURNALIST
WHO REVISITED THIS STORY
IN THE 1970s.
RON YATES,
ONCE THE TOKYO BUREAU CHIEF
OF THE CHICAGO TRIBUNE,
WROTE A SERIES OF ARTICLES
IN 1976
ON THE TOKYO ROSE TRIAL.
WE'VE AGREED TO MEET
AT THE JAPANESE AMERICAN
NATIONAL MUSEUM IN LOS ANGELES.
WELL, HERE'S THE RECORD
I WAS TELLING YOU ABOUT, RON.
OH, WOW, LOOK AT THAT.
I'M INVESTIGATING A MAN
NAMED HARRY BRUNDIDGE.
THEY MENTION HIM
ON THIS RECORDING.
DO YOU KNOW WHO HE WAS?
OH, YEAH, HARRY BRUNDIDGE IS
A VERY INTERESTING CHARACTER.
RON EXPLAINS
HOW HARRY BRUNDIDGE
HAD FIRST BECOME INVOLVED
WITH TOKYO ROSE
THREE YEARS BEFORE THE TRIAL
IN THE IMMEDIATE AFTERMATH
OF WORLD WAR II.
THAT'S WHEN BRUNDIDGE
HOOKED UP WITH
VETERAN WAR CORRESPONDENT
CLARK LEE.
THEY HEADED TO JAPAN
IN 1945
IN PURSUIT OF THE SCOOP
OF A LIFETIME.
THEY THOUGHT, "WE'LL FIND TOKYO
ROSE AND THAT'LL BE OUR STORY."
THEY SAID, "WE WILL PAY HER
$2,000 IF SHE'LL COME
TO THE IMPERIAL HOTEL
TO BE INTERVIEWED."
IN WAR-TORN TOKYO, WHERE
MOST PEOPLE WERE STARVING,
THAT MONEY MIGHT GET HER HOME
TO THE UNITED STATES.
BUT WHEN SHE WALKED
INTO THE ROOM,
THIS WAS NOT
WHAT THEY WERE EXPECTING.
IN HER PIGTAILS
AND SADDLE SHOES,
IVA NEITHER LOOKED
NOR SOUNDED THE PART
OF THE MATAHARI OF THE EAST.
RON SHOWS ME A REENACTMENT
OF A ZERO HOUR BROADCAST
THAT IVA LATER AGREED TO DO
FOR THE U.S. ARMY IN TOKYO.
Greetings, everybody.
This is your number-one enemy,
your favorite playmate,
Orphan Ann, ready again
for a vicious assault
on your morale.
RON EXPLAINS THAT
ALL THE SCRIPTS
WERE WRITTEN
BY ALLIED P.O.W.s,
WHO ALSO HAD BEEN FORCED
TO WORK FOR RADIO TOKYO.
THE LANGUAGE WAS INTENDED
TO BE TONGUE-IN-CHEEK,
THE KIND OF TEASING
THAT AMERICANS
WOULD EASILY RECOGNIZE.
AND THEY'D ALWAYS GO OVER
THE SCRIPTS WITH HER AND SAY,
"HERE'S WHAT WE WANT YOU
TO SAY, IVA."
AND THEN SHE WOULD SAY
THESE THINGS,
LIKE "HELLO, MY HONORABLE
BONEHEADS OF THE PACIFIC.
"THIS IS YOUR FAVORITE ENEMY,
ORPHAN ANN.
I'M GOING TO SNEAK UP BEHIND YOU
WITH MY NAIL FILE."
YOU SEE IN HER FACE THAT
SHE KNOWS SHE'S SAYING THINGS
THAT WOULD SOUND MEAN
TO THE JAPANESE
BUT THAT IT'S ACTUALLY AN INSIDE
JOKE AMONG ALL THE AMERICANS.
RIGHT, THERE'S A REAL
FACETIOUSNESS TO IT.
WHEN BRUNDIDGE AND LEE
INTERVIEWED IVA IN 1945,
THAT TEASING TONE NEVER MADE IT
INTO THEIR NOTES.
THEY HAD OTHER PLANS.
THE STORY JUST WASN'T THERE.
THIS WAS NOT THE SIREN
OF THE PACIFIC.
BRUNDIDGE TOOK OUT THE CONTRACT
FOR $2,000,
THEN ASKED IVA
A FATEFUL QUESTION.
"JUST FOR THE HECK OF IT,
WOULD YOU JUST SIGN THIS
AS TOKYO ROSE?"
AND SHE SAID, "SURE."
WHAT HE DID WAS
HE TOOK THOSE NOTES
AND GAVE THEM TO THE
OCCUPATION FORCES, AUTHORITIES,
AND SAID, "I HAVE THE SIGNED
CONFESSION OF TOKYO ROSE HERE."
AND WITHIN A FEW DAYS
SHE WAS ARRESTED.
SHE WAS FIRST IMPRISONED
IN TOKYO UNDER MARTIAL LAW
AND HELD FOR A YEAR
WHILE THE ARMY
COUNTER INTELLIGENCE CORPS
INVESTIGATED.
FINDING NO EVIDENCE
OF TREASON,
THE WAR DEPARTMENT CLEARED
AND FINALLY RELEASED HER.
THAT SHOULD HAVE BEEN
THE END OF IT.
SO BRUNDIDGE MET HER IN '45,
'46 SHE'S RELEASED FROM PRISON,
HOW DID IT BECOME A STORY
AGAIN IN 1948?
THAT IS A STORY IN ITSELF.
AFTER BEING FREED
BY THE U.S. ARMY,
IVA HAD APPLIED
FOR REPATRIATION.
BUT THE POPULAR RADIO HOST
WALTER WINCHELL
LEARNED OF THE REQUEST
AND STARTED A CAMPAIGN
TO PREVENT HER RETURN
AND TRY HER FOR TREASON.
GOLD STAR MOTHERS --
THESE ARE MOTHERS
WHO HAD LOST THEIR SONS
FIGHTING IN THE PACIFIC --
BEGAN WRITING
TO WALTER WINCHELL,
HE FORWARDED THOSE
TO THE TRUMAN ADMINISTRATION,
AND THAT PRESSURE BEGAN
TO BUILD.
IT WAS AN ELECTION YEAR.
RON SAYS CHARGES OF BEING SOFT
ON COMMUNISTS AND TRAITORS
WAS A CRITICAL FACTOR
IN TRUMAN'S CLOSE PRESIDENTIAL
RACE AGAINST THOMAS DEWEY.
THE TRUMAN ADMINISTRATION
DOESN'T WANT TO BE PERCEIVED
AS BEING SOFT ON TRAITORS.
THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE
ISSUED A REQUEST FOR WITNESSES
TO IVA'S ALLEGED ACTS
OF TREASON.
SO HERE COMES BRUNDIDGE AGAIN.
WHEN BRUNDIDGE MET UP WITH
ATTORNEY GENERAL TOM CLARK,
HE OFFERED TO GET
A NEW CONFESSION FROM IVA
AND TO FIND WITNESSES
TO HELP CONVICT HER.
TOM CLARK ASSIGNS SOME OF
HIS MINIONS TO GO BACK TO TOKYO,
AND HARRY BRUNDIDGE
GOES WITH THEM.
RON SAYS IT WASN'T UNTIL
A QUARTER-CENTURY
AFTER IVA'S TRIAL
THAT HE UNLOCKED
A CRUCIAL PIECE
OF THE GOVERNMENT'S STRATEGY.
RON ARRANGED TO MEET TWO MEN
WHO HAD HELD ON TO A SECRET:
GEORGE MITSUSHIO
AND KEN OKI,
IVA'S OLD BOSSES
FROM RADIO TOKYO.
THEY SAID, "WE -- OUR TESTIMONY
IS WHAT CONVICTED HER,
AND IT WAS ALL A LIE."
THEY HAD BEEN COACHED
FOR TWO MONTHS
BY THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
IN WHAT THEY SHOULD SAY
AT THE TRIAL.
AND THEIR TESTIMONY WAS
THE SIXTH OF THE EIGHT COUNTS
WHICH SHE WAS INDICTED ON,
THAT SHE DID SPEAK
INTO A MICROPHONE
ABOUT THE LOSS OF SHIPS.
BUT WHAT ABOUT
BRUNDIDGE'S CLAIMS
OF FINDING ADDITIONAL
SECRET WITNESSES?
I KNOW THE PERFECT PERSON
TO TELL YOU ABOUT THEM.
I'M MEETING WITH BARBARA
TREMBLEY AT DARKWOOD STUDIOS.
BARBARA MET IVA
20 YEARS AGO.
OVER TIME THEY BECAME FRIENDS.
IVA AGREED TO TELL
HER FULL STORY
AND GAVE BARBARA THE RIGHTS
TO MAKE HER SAGA
INTO A FEATURE FILM.
I HAVE A RECORDING
THAT IS DESCRIBING THE MOMENT
WHEN IVA COMES BACK
TO THE UNITED STATES.
I TELL BARBARA THAT
ON THIS RECORDING
BRUNDIDGE BOASTS OF GETTING IVA
TO SIGN A NEW CONFESSION.
WHY IS IVA EVEN WILLING
TO SEE HIM,
MUCH LESS TO SIGN
THIS DOCUMENT?
SHE HAD JUST LOST HER BABY.
BARBARA EXPLAINS THAT IVA
HAD JUST SUFFERED A MISCARRIAGE
AND DESPERATELY WANTED
TO GET HOME TO THE STATES.
IVA TOLD BARBARA THAT
BRUNDIDGE HAD ASSURED HER
THAT SIGNING THE DOCUMENT
WAS A PASSPORT HOME.
AND THEN AS SOON
AS SHE SIGNED IT,
BRUNDIDGE LEANED OVER TO IVA
AND HE SAID,
"YOU'VE DONE YOURSELF
A GOOD DEAL.
THEY'LL NEVER EXECUTE
A WOMAN."
SHE LOST HER HEART
AT THAT POINT.
BRUNDIDGE HAD WRITTEN
ABOUT SECRET WITNESSES
THAT WOULD PROVE THE CASE
AGAINST IVA.
YES, MR. YAGI.
YAGI WAS ACTUALLY SOMEONE
THAT BRUNDIDGE HAD KNOWN
BEFORE THE WAR.
BARBARA SAYS THAT WHEN
BRUNDIDGE TRAVELED TO JAPAN,
HIROM YAGI ACTED AS A FIXER,
MAKING LOCAL INTRODUCTIONS
FOR THE JOURNALIST.
BRUNDIDGE LITERALLY BRIBED HIM.
HE SAID, "YOU WILL GET
A TRIP TO THE U.S.
"AND WE'LL HAVE
A WONDERFUL TIME.
"ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS TESTIFY
FOR THE GRAND JURY,
AND THIS IS ALL
YOU HAVE TO SAY."
BARBARA FOUND
THE HANDWRITTEN TESTIMONY
YAGI HAD GIVEN BRUNDIDGE
AND THE U.S. ATTORNEY GENERAL.
"I HEARD HER SAY
INTO THE MICROPHONE,
'YOUR WIVES ARE OUT
WITH WAR WORKERS.'"
SO DOES HE TESTIFY
AT THE TRIAL
BEFORE THE GRAND JURY?
YES, HE DOES.
BUT AS SOON AS HE GETS BACK
TO JAPAN, HE RECANTS.
YAGI EVEN WRITES A LETTER
TO BRUNDIDGE
ASKING HIM TO PLEASE STOP THIS
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
"DEAR MR. BRUNDIDGE, THIS IS
AN ELEVENTH HOUR APPEAL
"ASKING YOU TO USE
YOUR GOOD INFLUENCES
TO CALL OFF THE COMING TRIAL,
IF POSSIBLE."
BARBARA EXPLAINS THAT BY NOW
THE GOVERNMENT
HAD SERIOUS DOUBTS
ABOUT BRUNDIDGE
AND EVEN BEGAN TO INVESTIGATE
HIM FOR WITNESS TAMPERING,
BUT THEY HAD TOO MUCH INVESTED
IN THE TRIAL TO BACK OUT NOW.
THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE,
TOM CLARK, AND SO ON,
THEY PUT A LID ON IT
AND IT BECAME A COVER-UP.
THE TRIAL PROCEEDED
AS PLANNED,
BUT DID IT GO ON
WITH BRUNDIDGE?
THAT'S WHEN IT BECOMES
VERY INTERESTING.
THE CONFIDENTIAL FILES
OF FBI DIRECTOR J. EDGAR HOOVER
WERE OPENED IN 2005.
IN THOSE DOCUMENTS
BARBARA HAS FOUND
SOME ANSWERS FOR BILL.
LET ME PLAY FOR YOU
WHAT'S ON YOUR RECORD,
AND THEN WE HEAR A VOICE
YOU MAY RECOGNIZE.
Brundidge on recording:
I went back at the request
of the attorney general
last March,
and Rose willingly signed it.
I RECOGNIZE HIS VOICE.
THAT WAS MY UNCLE HARRY.
I TELL BILL
ABOUT HIS UNCLE'S ROLE
IN LINKING
THE REAL-LIFE IVA TOGURI
AND THE FABLED TOKYO ROSE.
THAT'S SAD, ISN'T IT?
YEAH.
HE PROBABLY DID MOST ANYTHING
TO GET A STORY,
AND THAT WAS A BIG STORY.
YOU'D WANTED TO KNOW
WHAT PART
HARRY BRUNDIDGE PLAYED
IN THIS TRIAL.
WHEN HE MENTIONED THAT
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL'S OFFICE
HAD SENT HIM BACK,
THAT'S WHERE THE STORY BECOMES
LARGER THAN JUST YOUR UNCLE.
SO WHAT WAS BRUNDIDGE'S ROLE
IN THE TRIAL?
WELL, BRUNDIDGE HAD NO ROLE
IN THE TRIAL.
THEY DIDN'T ALLOW HIM
TO TESTIFY.
THE FBI,
THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE:
HE WAS SUCH A HOT POTATO,
NOBODY WANTED TO GET NEAR HIM.
ON ONE INTERNAL MEMO,
BARBARA DISCOVERED
THAT J. EDGAR HOOVER
HAD WEIGHED IN
ON BRUNDIDGE'S
SO-CALLED WITNESS
RECANTING HIS TESTIMONY.
"I'M NOT SURPRISED
AT DEVELOPMENTS.
"IT WAS MOST UNWISE
FOR DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE
TO USE SUCH A PERSON AS
BRUNDIDGE IN THE FIRST PLACE."
THEY REALIZED THE WHOLE CASE
COULD BE BLOWN UP
IF HE TESTIFIED.
HE FINALLY WENT TO THE DEFENSE
AND OFFERED TO TESTIFY FOR THEM,
AND THEY WOULDN'T TOUCH HIM
EITHER.
GEE, THAT'S SOMETHING ELSE.
YOU KNOW, BACK IN WAR TIMES,
PEOPLE LOOKED UPON
THE JAPANESE REALLY BAD,
AND IT DIDN'T MAKE
ANY DIFFERENCE
WHETHER THEY WERE AMERICANS
OR --
LOOK AT ALL THE INTERNEES THEY
HAD, AND THEY WERE GOOD PEOPLE.
THEY WERE.
BILL, I REALLY WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR GIVING ME THIS RECORD
AND GIVING ME A CHANCE
TO SEE THIS LARGER HISTORY.
THANK YOU.
I'M GLAD ALL THIS CAME OUT.
I APPRECIATE THE WISDOM
WITH WHICH YOU HEARD THE STORY.
GIVEN THE NEW PUBLIC
DISCLOSURES
ABOUT IVA'S INNOCENCE
AND THE PERJURED TESTIMONY
AGAINST HER,
PRESIDENT FORD AGREED
TO LOOK INTO HER CASE.
IN HIS LAST OFFICIAL ACT
IN OFFICE,
HE GRANTED IVA TOGURI A FULL
AND UNCONDITIONAL PARDON
ON JANUARY 19, 1977.
SHE PASSED AWAY
IN 2006.
TWELVE AMERICANS
WERE TRIED FOR TREASON
AFTER WORLD WAR II.
SEVEN WERE RADIO BROADCASTERS.
AXIS SALLY WAS ONE OF
THE MOST INFAMOUS.
BORN MILDRED GILLARS, SHE DREAMT
OF BECOMING A STARLET.
WITH LITTLE THEATER SUCCESS,
GILLARS MOVED TO GERMANY
IN THE MID-1930s
AND WORKED FOR RADIO BERLIN.
FROM DECEMBER 1941
TO MAY 1945,
GILLARS' SULTRY VOICE
REACHED AMERICAN G.I.s
WITH PRO-GERMAN WAR UPDATES
DESIGNED TO DEPLETE MORALE.
GILLARS' BROADCASTS CAME UNDER
THE AUSPICES OF JOSEPH GOEBBELS,
HITLER'S PROPAGANDA MINISTER.
SHE POSED AS AN AMERICAN
RED CROSS VOLUNTEER,
INTERVIEWING AMERICAN P.O.W.s
BUT DISTORTING THEIR COMMENTS.
SHE CRITICIZED ROOSEVELT
AND CHURCHILL
AND MUSED ABOUT
THE UNFAITHFULNESS
OF G.I. WIVES AND GIRLFRIENDS
BACK HOME.
AXIS SALLY'S
MOST INFAMOUS BROADCAST,
"VISION OF INVASION,"
TARGETED AMERICAN TROOPS
AWAITING D-DAY.
GILLARS PLAYED A G.I. MOTHER
DREAMING OF HER SON'S DEATH.
CRIES OF THE WOUNDED
PLAYED IN THE BACKGROUND,
CREATING THE IMPRESSION
OF IMPENDING SLAUGHTER.
The boys will be killed
or crippled for the rest
of their lives.
AFTER THE WAR, GILLARS WAS
EXTRADITED TO THE U.S.
SHE WAS FOUND GUILTY
OF TREASON
AND SENTENCED TO 10 TO 30 YEARS
IN PRISON.
IN 1961, GILLARS LEFT JAIL
TO LIVE IN A CONVENT
AND TEACH CATHOLIC SCHOOL.
SHE DIED IN 1988.
Elyse:
OUR NEXT STORY GOES IN SEARCH
OF A NATIVE-AMERICAN LEGEND.
MORE THAN 125 YEARS
AFTER HIS DEATH,
THE NAME CRAZY HORSE
STILL ECHOES
IN THE BLACK HILLS
OF SOUTH DAKOTA.
IN LIFE, THE LAKOTA WARRIOR
AND SPIRITUAL MAN
VOWED TO PROTECT
THESE SACRED HUNTING GROUNDS
FROM ENCROACHING SETTLERS
AND GOLD MINERS.
IN 1876, HE HELPED CRUSH
THE U.S. CAVALRY TROOPS
OF GENERAL GEORGE CUSTER AT THE
BATTLE OF THE LITTLE BIGHORN.
BUT IS THIS A TRUE LIKENESS
OF THE WARRIOR?
DESPITE HIS FAME, CRAZY HORSE
REFUSED TO BE PHOTOGRAPHED,
SHUNNING WHITES
AND THEIR TECHNOLOGIES.
FOR YEARS, RUMORS
OF CRAZY HORSE PHOTOGRAPHS
HAVE TANTALIZED COLLECTORS.
MORE THAN 125 YEARS
AFTER THE WARRIOR'S DEATH,
TIM GIAGO
OF RAPID CITY, SOUTH DAKOTA,
HAS A FRAMED IMAGE
WHICH MAY BE
THE ONLY PHOTOGRAPHIC IMAGE
OF THIS LEGEND.
IT SAID, "TASUNKA WITKO,"
AND TASUNKA WITKO
IS THE LAKOTA NAME
THAT MEANS CRAZY HORSE.
I'M MEETING TIM AT HIS HOME
TO FIND OUT MORE.
HI.
WELCOME TO MY HOUSE.
THANK YOU.
WELL, ABOUT 27 YEARS AGO,
A CONSTRUCTION MANAGER CAME INTO
MY NEWSPAPER, THE LAKOTA TIMES,
AND HE HAD THIS WITH HIM.
ONE OF HIS EMPLOYEES,
A LAKOTA MAN,
HAD PUT IT IN HOCK
AND SAID HE COULD HAVE IT
IF HE WENT DOWN
AND TOOK IT OUT OF PAWN.
SO HE BROUGHT IT DOWN
TO MY NEWSPAPER.
ALONG WITH THAT WAS THIS LETTER
WHICH IS DATED 1904.
IT'S WRITTEN ENTIRELY
IN THE VERY OLD LAKOTA LANGUAGE.
IT SAYS THAT "TASUNKA WITKO,"
WHICH MEANS CRAZY HORSE.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW SPECIFICALLY
ABOUT CRAZY HORSE?
CRAZY HORSE WAS REALLY
ONE OF THE GREAT WARRIORS
OF THE LAKOTA.
PEOPLE SAID THAT BULLETS
COULDN'T HIT HIM.
ONE OF THE REASONS
HE'S SO ADMIRED AND LOVED
BY THE LAKOTA PEOPLE TODAY
IS HE WOULD NEVER SIGN A TREATY.
HE NEVER SOLD OUT ANY LAND
OR ANY OF HIS PEOPLE,
AND TO ME THAT'S
HIGHLY ADMIRABLE.
BUT WHAT CRAZY HORSE LOOKS LIKE
HAS LONG BEEN A MYSTERY.
DO YOU KNOW OF ANY OTHER
PHOTOGRAPHS OF CRAZY HORSE?
I'VE NEVER SEEN ONE.
I'VE SEEN PHOTOGRAPHS
THAT WERE DISPROVED,
THAT THAT'S NOT CRAZY HORSE,
ALWAYS PROVED TO BE
SOMEONE ELSE.
I WOULD LIKE YOU
TO FIND OUT VERY MUCH
WHETHER THIS IS INDEED
A TRUE PICTURE OF CRAZY HORSE.
[ ♪♪♪ ]
IT'S JUST AS TIM SUGGESTED.
THERE ARE A NUMBER
OF DISPUTED IMAGES
CLAIMING TO BE CRAZY HORSE.
MOST OF THEM HAVE
PRETTY SHAKY STORIES,
AND NONE RESEMBLE OUR GUY.
THERE'S NOTHING OBVIOUS
TO SUGGEST OUR MAN
IS EVEN A WARRIOR CHIEF,
NO WAR BONNET
OR ELABORATE DECORATION.
HE DOES HAVE A COLLAR ON
AND AN EAGLE FEATHER,
BUT BESIDES THAT,
HE'S DRESSED PRETTY PLAINLY.
I'M TRYING TO TAKE
THE BACK OFF CAREFULLY.
IT LOOKS LIKE THERE'S
MORE LAKOTA WRITING
ALONG WITH THE DATE, 1875.
AH, NOW, THIS IS HELPFUL.
HERE AGAIN, "CRAZY HORSE"
AND "1875" IN HANDWRITING.
BUT THERE'S ALSO
A STAMPED NAME AND ADDRESS.
"ALEX GARDNER, 921 PENNSYLVANIA
AVENUE, WASHINGTON, D.C."
LET ME DO SOME DIGGING.
THERE WAS AN ALEXANDER GARDNER
WHO WAS A CELEBRATED
PHOTOGRAPHER
IN THE 19th CENTURY.
HE PHOTOGRAPHED
ABRAHAM LINCOLN.
I'M NOT CERTAIN
THEY WERE THE SAME PERSON,
BUT ALEXANDER GARDNER
WAS A SCOTTISH SOCIALIST
WHO HAD GOTTEN INTERESTED
IN PHOTOGRAPHY
AFTER SEEING
MATTHEW BRADY'S WORK.
BRADY AND GARDNER BECAME
THE TWO BEST KNOWN
PHOTOGRAPHERS OF THE CIVIL WAR.
BUT IT SEEMS THAT A NUMBER
OF GARDNER'S BATTLEFIELD IMAGES
FROM THE WAR
WERE CONTROVERSIAL.
HE ACTUALLY MOVED BODIES
ON THE CIVIL WAR BATTLEFIELDS
TO BETTER SUIT
HIS PHOTOGRAPHIC NEEDS.
AND THIS IS INTERESTING:
GARDNER TRAVELED TO
THE LAKOTA TERRITORIES IN 1868
TO PHOTOGRAPH NEGOTIATIONS
BETWEEN NORTHERN PLAIN TRIBES
AND THE GOVERNMENT.
THE FORT LARAMIE TREATY
ESTABLISHED
THE GREAT SIOUX RESERVATION
AND PROTECTED THE BLACK HILLS
FOR THE LAKOTA.
IT'S POSSIBLE THAT THIS IS
AN ALEXANDER GARDNER PHOTOGRAPH
AND THAT GARDNER MET
CRAZY HORSE,
BUT THE DATE ON OUR PHOTO,
IF IT'S ACCURATE,
IS SEVEN YEARS AFTER
GARDNER PHOTOGRAPHED
THE LAKOTA TREATIES.
I THINK THE FIRST THING
THAT I NEED TO DO
IS FIGURE OUT EXACTLY
WHAT THIS NOTE SAYS.
I'M HEADED TO
OGLALA LAKOTA COLLEGE
IN RAPID CITY.
LAKOTA LANGUAGE AND CULTURE
PROFESSOR WILMER MESTETH
IS SKEPTICAL OF OUR IMAGE.
HE EXPLAINS WHY CRAZY HORSE
REJECTED PHOTOGRAPHY.
IN ORAL HISTORY THEY SAID
HE MADE A STATEMENT
THAT THESE PHOTOGRAPHS
WERE EVIL
AND THAT ANYBODY
THAT TOOK THEIR PHOTOGRAPH,
THEIR SOUL WAS CAPTURED
IN THE PICTURE.
CRAZY HORSE'S REJECTION
OF THE WHITE MAN'S TECHNOLOGY
WAS PART OF HIS DEFENSE OF THE
BESIEGED LAKOTA WAY OF LIFE.
THE 1868 TREATY
OF FORT LARAMIE
HAD GUARANTEED THE LAKOTA
THEIR TRIBAL LANDS,
BUT JUST SIX YEARS LATER,
THE TREATY WOULD BE VIOLATED.
IN 1874,
THERE WAS AN EXPEDITION
THAT CAME DOWN INTO THE
BLACK HILLS IN SEARCH OF GOLD,
LED BY GENERAL CUSTER,
AND THEY DID FIND GOLD
IN THE BLACK HILLS.
TWO YEARS LATER,
IN JUNE 1876,
CRAZY HORSE HELPED DEFEAT
GENERAL CUSTER
AT THE BATTLE
OF THE LITTLE BIGHORN.
IT WAS THE WORST U.S. MILITARY
DEFEAT OF THE INDIAN WARS.
ALTHOUGH MANY
SIOUX CONTEMPORARIES
WERE PHOTOGRAPHED,
THE LAKOTA HAVE RELIED
ON ORAL HISTORY
FOR A DESCRIPTION
OF CRAZY HORSE.
THEY SAID HE WAS
OF MEDIUM HEIGHT,
HIS HAIR WAS LIGHT IN COLOR,
AND HIS COMPLEXION WAS LIGHT.
AND HE HAD A MYSTERIOUS AURA
ABOUT HIM.
THEY SAID YOU COULD ALMOST FEEL
HIS PRESENCE AND HIS STRENGTH
AS A POWERFUL MAN.
THIS IS THE LETTER
THAT CAME WITH THE PHOTOGRAPH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THIS LETTER IS WRITTEN
IN OLD LAKOTA ORTHOGRAPHY,
IN LAKOTA LANGUAGE.
WILMER TELLS ME THAT OLD LAKOTA
WAS USED FOR A HUNED YEARS,
UNTIL ABOUT 1960.
[ reading in Lakota ]
"THIS PHOTOGRAPH IS
A PHOTOGRAPH OF CRAZY HORSE."
WHAT ELSE DOES IT SAY?
[ reading in Lakota ]
"THE WAY YOU WOULD RECOGNIZE
THAT THIS IS HE
IS THERE IS A SCAR
ON HIS LEFT CHEEK."
IS IT TRUE THAT CRAZY HORSE
HAD A SCAR?
YES, CRAZY HORSE WAS SHOT
BY A MAN CALLED NO WATER
IN A JEALOUS RAGE.
HE SHOT TO KILL CRAZY HORSE
BUT GRAZED HIM ON THE LEFT SIDE
OF THE CHEEK.
THE MAN ON THE PHOTO
IS FAVORING HIS RIGHT.
IF THERE'S A SCAR ON THE LEFT,
I CAN'T TELL.
THEN IT SAYS, "WE WERE WITH
CRAZY HORSE WAY BACK THEN.
THIS IS ME, DEWEY BEARD."
WILMER THINKS THAT
DEWEY BEARD
MAY HAVE DICTATED THE STORY
TO SOMEONE,
POSSIBLY TO THIS B.B.E.
SIGNED AT THE BOTTOM.
AND WHO WAS DEWEY BEARD?
DEWEY BEARD WAS THERE
AT THE LITTLE BIGHORN
AT THE AGE OF 10 YEARS OLD.
AND POSSIBLY KNEW
CRAZY HORSE.
I'M PRETTY SURE THIS PERSON
KNEW CRAZY HORSE, YES.
IN YOUR OPINION, DO YOU THINK
THERE'S ANY POSSIBILITY
THAT THIS COULD BE
CRAZY HORSE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
THIS PERSON IN THIS PHOTOGRAPH
IS OF DARKER COMPLEXION.
CRAZY HORSE HIMSELF
WAS LIGHT-COMPLECTED.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT
TO MAKE OF THIS.
WILMER THINKS THE NOTE
IS LEGITIMATE.
STILL, HISTORY'S VERDICT
STANDS IN OUR WAY.
NOBODY'S EVER PRODUCED A
PHOTOGRAPH OF CRAZY HORSE, EVER.
WILMER SUGGESTED I VISIT
THE CRAZY HORSE MEMORIAL
IN THE BLACK HILLS.
SCULPTOR KORCZAK ZIOLKOWSKI
BEGAN THE MASSIVE CARVING
IN THE 1940s...
AND TODAY IT REMAINS
THE WORLD'S LARGEST
MOUNTAIN SCULPTURE
IN PROGRESS.
THE MONUMENT IS A TESTAMENT TO
THE IMPORTANCE OF HIS MEMORY,
BUT WHERE IS THE PHYSICAL MODEL
FOR THE MASSIVE FACE?
DOUG WAR EAGLE IS
CRAZY HORSE'S GRANDSON.
HOW WAS THE MONUMENT BUILT?
I MEAN, HOW DO WE KNOW
WHAT HE LOOKS LIKE?
IT'S JUST THE CLOSEST REPLICA
OF HIM.
THERE NEVER WAS A PHOTO
EVER TAKEN OF OUR GRANDFATHER.
HE SAYS THE MONUMENT REPRESENTS
CRAZY HORSE'S SPIRIT
RATHER THAN HIS EXACT IMAGE.
WHEN I SHOW DOUG OUR PHOTO,
RIGHT AWAY HE'S SKEPTICAL.
THIS MAN HAS AN EAGLE FEATHER
IN HIS HAIR.
OUR GRANDFATHER NEVER WORE
AN EAGLE FEATHER IN HIS HAIR.
OUR GRANDPA WEARS
THE RED-TAILED HAWK FEATHER
WITH THE BUFFALO BONE.
DOUG'S BROUGHT SOMETHING
TO SHOW ME
THAT FEW OUTSIDE HIS FAMILY
HAVE SEEN.
I'VE BROUGHT TWO SKETCHES
OF OUR GRANDFATHER'S.
THE FIRST ONE IS WAGLULA,
OLD MAN CRAZY HORSE.
HE SAYS THE WARRIOR
CRAZY HORSE
WAS ACTUALLY THE THIRD MAN
TO CARRY THAT NAME.
IN ACCORDANCE
WITH LAKOTA TRADITION,
CRAZY HORSE INHERITED THE NAME
FROM THIS MAN, HIS FATHER,
WHEN HE BECAME A WARRIOR.
AND THE OTHER SKETCH I HAVE HERE
IS OF THE WARRIOR.
IT WAS SKETCHED LONG AFTER
HIS DEATH IN 1934,
WHEN CRAZY HORSE'S
YOUNGER SISTER
DESCRIBED HIS APPEARANCE
TO A FORENSIC ARTIST.
THE LIKENESS TRIGGERED
AN EMOTIONAL REACTION.
SHE CRIED, BECAUSE SHE SAID
THAT'S THE CLOSEST LIKENESS
THAT YOU WILL EVER HAVE
OF HIM.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
WELL, HE CERTAINLY DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE OUR PHOTOGRAPH.
SO IT HAS THE TWO FEATHERS,
THE LONG, FLOWING HAIR,
AND A LITTLE BIT
OF A SCAR.
THAT'S THE CLOSEST
WE'LL EVER GET
OF OUR GRANDFATHER,
THE WARRIOR,
THE ONE THAT FOUGHT
THE BATTLE OF LITTLE BIGHORN.
DOUG IS CONVINCED OUR IMAGE
ISN'T CRAZY HORSE.
BUT THIS SKETCH
WAS MADE BY SOMEONE
WHO NEVER MET CRAZAZY HORSE,
SIX DECADES AFTER HE DIED.
I'M TAKING THE IMAGE
TO THE SMITHSONIAN,
WHICH HOUSES
THE WORLD'S LARGEST ARCHIVE
OF NATIVE-AMERICAN PHOTOGRAPHS.
I WANT TO SHOW IT TO ONE
OF THE SMITHSONIAN'S CURATORS.
BUT FIRST,
BECAUSE THERE HAVE BEEN
MANY BOGUS
CRAZY HORSE PICTURES,
WHILE I'M HERE,
I ALSO WANT TO SHOW IT
TO STAFF PHOTOGRAPHER
DON HURLBURT.
WELCOME TO THE DARKROOM.
WOW.
OKAY, SO HERE'S MY PIECE,
AND ON THE BACK IT SAYS 1875.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU THOUGHT
IT WAS PERIOD.
IT DEFINITELY HAS
CHARACTERISTICS
FROM THAT TIME FRAME.
IT'S YELLOWING, IT'S GOT
A GOOD GOLD TONE TO IT.
IT HAS THE SHININESS
ON THE SURFACE OF THE PRINT
THAT A MODERN PRINT
WOULD NOT HAVE
BUT PRINTS OF THAT AGE DO.
HOW WOULD A PRINT LIKE THIS
HAVE BEEN MADE IN THE 1870s?
IT WAS DEFINITELY A MULTI-DAY,
MULTI-STEP PROCESS
TO MAKE ONE OF THESE PRINTS.
THESE GUYS DID A LOT OF WORK
TO GET THESE PHOTOGRAPHS.
THESE PRINTS CAME
FROM GLASS PLATE NEGATIVES
THAT WERE MADE, PRODUCED FROM
ABOUT THE 1850s TO 1880s.
WELL, I CAN SHOW YOU.
THE INVENTION OF GLASS PLATES
MEANT THAT FOR THE FIRST TIME,
PHOTOGRAPHERS LIKE GARDNER
HAD A PHOTOGRAPHIC MEDIUM
FROM WHICH TO MAKE
UNLIMITED NUMBERS OF PRINTS.
GLASS PLATES REVOLUTIONIZED
PHOTOGRAPHY.
NOW THAT I'VE CLEANED IT
AND CHECKED IT,
WE'RE GOING TO BRING IT
OVER HERE, SET IT DOWN,
GET A SHEET OF MODERN PAPER OUT,
BECAUSE WE DO NOT HAVE
ANY OF THE ALBUMEN PAPER
WITH US ANYMORE.
DON SAYS GARDNER, OR WHOEVER
TOOK THE PHOTOGRAPH,
WOULD HAVE MADE
ALBUMEN SILVER PRINTS,
WHICH EXPOSED
IN SUNLIGHT.
TODAY, USING MODERN
PHOTO PAPER,
DEVELOPING A PRINT IN THE
DARKROOM TAKES MERE MINUTES.
THAT'S GREAT.
I LEARN MORE ABOUT THE PRINT
FROM FORMER ARCHIVIST
AND SMITHSONIAN VOLUNTEER
PAULA FLEMING.
SHE SAYS THE IMAGE WAS ALMOST
CERTAINLY TAKEN BY GARDNER
NOT OUT WEST
BUT ON THE EAST COAST
AT THE ADDRESS
ON THE BACK OF OUR PHOTOGRAPH.
HE HAD A STUDIO
IN WASHINGTON, D.C.,
AND HE TOOK MOST OF HIS
INDIAN PORTRAITS THERE.
WELL, WHAT WOULD BRING THEM
TO WASHINGTON, D.C.?
AFTER THE CIVIL WAR,
THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT
RENEWED ITS EFFORTS
TO DEAL WITH THE INDIANS
TO RESOLVE ISSUES OF LAND
ACQUISITION AND ANNUITIES.
PAULA SAYS HUNDREDS
OF AMERICAN INDIANS
WERE INVITED TO WASHINGTON
AS TRIBAL DELEGATIONS.
THE GOVERNMENT WANTED
TO SHOW THE INDIANS
THE BENEFITS OF CIVILIZATION,
SO THEY TOOK THEM ON TRAINS
AND THEY TOOK THEM TO BIG CITIES
TO SHOW THEM WHAT IT WAS LIKE
TO BE CIVILIZED.
ON THE SURFACE,
THE WASHINGTON VISITS
WERE EFFORTS TO PEACEFULLY
RESOLVE LAND DISPUTES
AND DEMONSTRATE
THAT THE INDIANS
WERE BEING TREATED
RESPECTFULLY,
BUT PAULA SAYS THE VISITS
OFTEN INCLUDED A STOP
WHICH HAD A POLITICAL AGENDA.
THEY WOULD ALSO TAKE THEM
TO THE ARSENAL
AND THEY'D SHOW THEM
STOCKPILES
OF WEAPONS AND CANNONBALLS
AND THEY WOULD HAVE DISPLAYS
OF MILITARY MIGHT.
THE GOVERNMENT WANTED
TO SHOW THEM
THAT IT WAS ACTUALLY FUTILE
TO FIGHT FOR THEIR LANDS.
THEY WERE GOING TO LOSE?
THEY WERE GOING TO LOSE.
CRAZY HORSE'S GRANDSON
HAD TOLD ME
THAT THE CLOTHING
AND DECORATION IN OUR IMAGE
WAS NOT TYPICAL
FOR THE WARRIOR.
BUT PAULA SAYS NOT ALL THE
PHOTOGRAPHS TAKEN IN WASHINGTON
WERE WHAT THEY APPEARED TO BE.
SOME PHOTOGRAPHERS
ACTUALLY KEPT PROPS
TO MAKE SURE THAT THE INDIANS
LOOKED EXOTIC ENOUGH,
AND SOMETIMES THEY PUT
THE IMPROPER COSTUMES
ON THE WRONG CULTURES.
PAULA HAS A SURPRISE FOR ME.
WITH THOUSANDS OF PHOTOGRAPHS
IN THE ARCHIVES,
IT CAN BE A LITTLE DAUNTING
IF YOU DON'T HAVE A NAME.
BUT I DID A LITTLE BIT
OF RESEARCH, AND COME HERE,
I'VE GOT SOMETHING
TO SHOW YOU.
WOW!
IT'S A GLASS PLATE NEGATIVE,
JUST LIKE THE ONE
DON SHOWED ME.
IT'S THE EXACT SAME IMAGE.
SURE IS.
THIS NEGATIVE WAS USED
TO PRINT THAT IMAGE.
IS IT CRAZY HORSE?
WHAT PAULA TELLS ME NEXT
CLOSES THE CASE.
WELL, TIM, IT WAS
AN INCREDIBLE INVESTIGATION.
I TELL HIM HE HAS AN AUTHENTIC
ALEXANDER GARDNER PHOTO,
ONE OF THE NATION'S
MOST CELEBRATED
PERIOD PHOTOGRAPHERS.
THERE ARE A LOT OF EXPERTS
THAT DON'T BELIEVE
THAT CRAZY HORSE
WAS EVER PHOTOGRAPHED,
AND THAT MADE IT
REALLY DIFFICULT.
FINALLY, THOUGH,
I WAS ABLE TO IDENTIFY
THE MAN IN YOUR PHOTOGRAPH
BY TRAVELING
TO WASHINGTON, D.C.,
JUST LIKE HE DID
150 YEARS AGO.
THERE WAS AN ENGLISHMAN BY THE
NAME OF WILLIAM HENRY BLACKMORE,
AND HE COMMISSIONED GARDNER
TO PHOTOGRAPH
THE DELEGATIONS OF INDIANS.
AND HE ALSO PUBLISHED
THE IMAGES.
THAT'S OUR GUY.
THE MAN IN THE PHOTOGRAPH
IS VUA-SHA-PEH,
WHOSE ENGLISH NAME
IS STABBER,
AND HE WAS AN OGLALA LAKOTA
WHO CAME TO WASHINGTON, D.C.,
WITH RED CLOUD
ON A DELEGATION.
THE MAN IN THIS PHOTOGRAPHED
HAD WITNESSED
ONE OF THE LAST
PEACEFUL NEGOTIATIONS
BETWEEN THE LAKOTA
AND THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT
BEFORE GOLD WAS DISCOVERED
IN THE BLACK HILLS.
HE WAS AN IMPORTANT PART
OF LAKOTA HISTORY.
I THINK IT'S GREAT
THAT WE KNOW WHO HE IS NOW.
VUA-SHA-PEH HAD TRAVELED
TO WASHINGTON
WITH RED CLOUD
AND THE LAKOTA DELEGATION.
IN CONTRAST, CRAZY HORSE
REJECTED DIPLOMACY
AND DEFENDED LAKOTA TRADITIONS
AS A WARRIOR TO THE END.
EXPERTS SAY THAT HE NEVER WENT
TO WASHINGTON;
HE STAYED ON HIS LAND
TO FIGHT FOR HIS PEOPLE
AND TO FIGHT
THE U.S. MILITARY.
I'M A GREAT ADMIRER
OF CRAZY HORSE,
AND I REALLY HOPED
THAT THIS WAS HIM.
WELL, I GUESS WE'LL NEVER KNOW
WHAT CRAZY HORSE LOOKED LIKE.
I HOPE THAT I CAN TAKE
THE PHOTOGRAPH
AND FIND HIS DESCENDANTS
AND PASS THE PHOTOGRAPH
DOWN TO THEM.
WE THANK YOU FOR COMING
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE
TO GIVE US THE NEWS.
AFTER HIS VICTORY
AT THE LITTLE BIGHORN,
CRAZY HORSE FOUGHT ON
UNTIL THE SPRING OF 1877.
THEN, HIS PEOPLE WEAKENED
BY WAR AND HUNGER,
HE SURRENDERED
AT CAMP ROBINSON, NEBRASKA.
ON SEPTEMBER 5, 1877,
HE WAS ARRESTED AND BROUGHT
INTO THE GUARD HOUSE.
REALIZING HE WAS
ABOUT TO BE LOCKED UP,
CRAZY HORSE STRUGGLED
AND WAS STABBED
BY A SOLDIER
WITH A BAYONET.
HE DIED LATE THAT NIGHT,
AND SOON AFTER,
HIS BODY WAS RETURNED
TO HIS ELDERLY PARENTS.
TO THIS DAY, HIS FINAL
BURIAL PLACE IS UNKNOWN,
BUT HIS SPIRIT LIVES ON
IN THE BLACK HILLS.
REPATRIATION RAISES
COMPLEX ISSUES
ABOUT CULTURAL HERITAGE
AND WHO OWNS IT.
TODAY, LITERALLY MILLIONS
OF AMERICAN INDIAN ARTIFACTS
ARE HOUSED IN NON-NATIVE MUSEUMS
AND PRIVATE COLLECTIONS.
MANY OF THESE OBJECTS, LIKE
TOOLS, WEAPONS, AND CLOTHES,
WERE ACQUIRED THROUGH
PERFECTLY LEGAL MEANS.
OTHERS, HOWEVER, WERE BOUGHT
FOR PENNIES OR STOLEN.
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT SAW
NOTHING WRONG WITH THIS,
SINCE ITS OFFICIAL POSITION
ON THE TRIBES
WAS TO TRY TO ASSIMILATE THEM
INTO THE MAINSTREAM.
BUT NATIVE PEOPLES
ARE STILL WITH US,
AND SOME HAVE BEGUN TO ASK FOR
-- EVEN DEMAND --
THEIR MOST IMPORTANT
ARTIFACTS BACK.
SO IN 1990, THE U.S. GOVERNMENT
SIGNED INTO LAW
THE NATIVE AMERICAN
GRAVE PROTECTION
AND REPATRIATION ACT,
OR NAGPRA.
NAGPRA REQUIRES
FEDERALLY FUNDED ORGANIZATIONS
TO RETURN SKELETONS AND OBJECTS
OF CULTURAL PATRIMONY
TO TRIBAL REPRESENTATIVES
IF THEY FOLLOW
THE CORRECT PROCEDURES.
NAGPRA ONLY APPLIES TO
FEDERALLY FUNDED ORGANIZATIONS.
PRIVATE COLLECTIONS
OR MUSEUMS ABROAD
DON'T FALL UNDER
ITS JURISDICTION.
DESPITE THESE CHALLENGES,
BOTH THE TRIBES AND MUSEUMS
SEE NAGPRA AS A STEP FORWARD.
Wes:
IN AN ENCORE PRESENTATION,
OUR FINAL STORY TURNS THE PAGES
OF A LONG-LOST DIARY
FROM A WORLD WAR II
BOMBER PILOT.
DECEMBER 13, 1943:
THE U.S. ARMY AIR FORCE
445th BOMB GROUP
ATTACKS ENEMY SHIPYARDS
BENEATH THE SKIES
OF KIEL, GERMANY.
IT'S THEIR FIRST
OF 280 AIR-RAID MISSIONS
INSIDE A NEW BOMBER
CALLED THE B-24 LIBERATOR.
THE BOMBER IS
THE ALLIES' GREAT HOPE,
FLYING FARTHER, LONGER,
AND CARRYING MORE BOMBS
DEEP INTO HITLER'S
GERMANY.
NOT A SINGLE PLANE IS LOST
ON THIS MISSION,
BUT THE 445th WILL RARELY
BE SO LUCKY AGAIN.
THE LIBERATOR EARNS ITSELF
ANOTHER MORE OMINOUS NICKNAME:
THE FLYING COFFIN,
DUE TO THE HIGH CASUALTY RATE
AMONG B-24 PILOTS.
WHY WERE THESE MISSIONS
SO DEADLY,
AND WHAT CONVINCED THEIR CREW
TO ACCEPT SUCH TERRIBLE ODDS?
SIXTY YEARS AFTER THE LAST
OF THOSE MISSIONS,
JIM CHAPMAN
OF LEXINGTON, NORTH CAROLINA,
HAS A DIARY THAT MAY REVEAL
NEW INFORMATION
ABOUT THESE PLANES AND MEN
WHO HELD HITLER AT BAY.
I'M WES COWAN,
AND I'M HEADING TO MEET JIM.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS DIARY.
MY DAD BROUGHT THIS
HOME WITH HIM
AFTER HE FINISHED
HIS TOUR OF DUTY
DURING WORLD WAR II.
AND THE OBVIOUS QUESTION
TO ME IS,
IT'S NOT YOUR DAD'S DIARY.
THAT'S CORRECT.
THE DIARY BELONGED TO HIS
CO-PILOT NAMED WILLIAM MORAN.
BOTH SERVED ON A B-24.
BOTH MEN FLEW PLANES
IN THE 445th BOMB GROUP
STATIONED IN
TIBENHAM, ENGLAND.
HOW DID YOUR DAD
GET IT?
WELL, THAT'S
A GOOD QUESTION.
I ACTUALLY DISCOVERED
THE DIARY
IN A BOX
OF MY FATHER'S MEMENTOS.
HE DISCOVERED IT AFTER
HIS FATHER DIED 20 YEARS AGO.
CAN YOU READ ME
SOME ENTRIES?
YES, I'D BE GLAD TO.
"SURE DREADED GOING,
"ESPECIALLY AFTER I FOUND
THE TARGET TO BE HAMBURG.
"FELT SURE
I WOULDN'T GET BACK.
"AT LEAST I KNOW NOW THAT
I'LL BE ABLE TO FACE DEATH
"WHEN MY TIME COMES.
"THE ONLY THING THAT I FEARED
WAS LEAVING JAYNE.
I ADORE HER EVERY BREATH."
MARY JAYNE
WAS MORAN'S WIFE.
IT'S THESE PERSONAL DETAILS
IN THE DIARY THAT HAUNT JIM.
"MAY 9, 1944.
"AN AIRMAIL LETTER
FROM MY ANGEL.
"MY BABY IS PRETTY SURE
SHE IS PREGNANT.
"THANK GOD!
"BOUGHT THE BOYS BEER
WITH MY LAST SIX SHILLINGS
TO CELEBRATE."
THAT'S REALLY GREAT.
THERE'S SOMETHING IMPORTANT
MISSING FROM THIS DIARY:
AN ENDING.
THE LAST ENTRY IS
FROM OCTOBER 29th,
SEVEN MONTHS BEFORE THE END
OF THE WAR IN EUROPE.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
WELL, WES, I'D LIKE TO FIND OUT
WHAT HAPPENED TO BILL MORAN,
IF HE CAME BACK HOME
OR IF HE WAS KILLED.
I'D LIKE TO REALLY KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM.
JIM IS EAGER
TO KNOW MORE ABOUT
WHAT THE MEN HIS FATHER FLEW
WITH SAW AND DID
DURING THEIR TIME
IN ENGLAND.
AND HE WANTS HELP
WITH ANOTHER QUESTION, TOO.
I WOULD LIKE TO BE ABLE
TO REUNITE THE DIARY
WITH BILL MORAN'S FAMILY.
I THINK IT'S VERY IMPORTANT
FOR THE FAMILY TO HAVE THIS.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE
THE DIARY WITH ME,
AND I'M READY TO GET GOING.
WELL, LET'S SEE.
EVERY TIME I READ ONE
OF THESE SOLDIER'S DIARIES,
I JUST GET THE SENSE
THAT I'M HOLDING A PIECE
OF HISTORY IN MY HAND.
THE DIARY COVERS
ABOUT A YEAR,
FROM OCTOBER 1943
TO OCTOBER 1944.
MUCH OF IT
IS WRITTEN MECHANICALLY,
MORE LIKE A LOG
THAN A PERSONAL JOURNAL.
BUT IT'S CLEAR HIS UNIT IS
IN THE THICK OF THE ACTION.
HERE'S ONE,
SEPTEMBER 27th.
"STARTED A LETTER
TO MY ANGEL,
"BUT BAHN STOPPED IN
TO TELL ME
"OUR SQUAD LOST
FOUR OUT OF NINE.
IT WAS WITHEY'S LAST ONE."
A LOT OF BOMBERS WENT DOWN
WITH MEN MORAN KNEW.
IF HE'S SHAKEN BY THIS,
I WOULDN'T KNOW IT
FROM THE MATTER-OF-FACT
LANGUAGE.
AND HERE'S BILL MORAN'S
LAST ENTRY,
OCTOBER 29, 1944.
MORE DEATH AND MORE
MATTER-OF-FACT LANGUAGE.
BILL WRITES,
"MASS AND COMMUNION.
"PUT A COUPLE HOURS
ON A SHIP.
"HEARD A ROTTEN GERMAN BROADCAST
LATE LAST NIGHT
CALLING EISENHOWER
A RAT."
BUT THERE ARE NO CLUES
WHY MORAN STOPPED WRITING.
DID HE GO BACK HOME OR WAS
HIS NEXT MISSION FATAL?
THERE ARE PLENTY
OF NAMES HERE.
MAYBE SOMEONE BILL MORAN
WROTE ABOUT IS STILL ALIVE
AND CAN FILL IN
THESE BLANK PAGES FOR ME.
"LENNY," IT LOOKS LIKE.
"GOLDEN."
"CHAPPY, PELTON, AND I
WERE LUCKY NOT TO GO."
I'LL CALL MY OFFICE AND ASK
THEM TO TRY TO TRACK DOWN
SOME OF BILL MORAN'S
WAR BUDDIES.
WES COWAN.
BILL OLDSON.
GLAD TO MEET YOU, WES.
WHILE THEY'RE SEARCHING,
I'VE COME TO FLORIDA
TO MEET WITH PROFESSOR
WILLIAM OLDSON
FROM THE INSTITUTE
ON WORLD WAR II
AND THE HUMAN EXPERIENCE.
HERE'S THE DIARY THAT I SENT YOU
THE TRANSCRIPT OF.
OH, NICE.
VERY UNUSUAL COVER.
AND IF I MUST SAY,
HIS HANDWRITING'S
BETTER THAN MOST, TOO.
WILLIAM SAYS UNEARTHING
JOURNALS FROM THE BATTLEFRONT
IS ALWAYS
AN IMPORTANT DISCOVERY,
A UNIQUE WINDOW ON THE MEN
WHO ACTUALLY DID THE FIGHTING.
IT'S THE UNVARNISHED TRUTH,
AND IT'S THE YARDSTICK YOU CAN
HOLD UP TO EVERYTHING ELSE --
TO THE LETTERS HOME,
TO THE PROPAGANDA,
TO THE NEWSREEL --
AND SAY, "HERE'S
WHAT HE FELT."
AND THERE CERTAINLY WAS
A LOT TO WRITE ABOUT.
WILLIAM EXPLAINS THAT
IN 1943,
ALLIED BOMBING RAIDS ON GERMANY
ARE OFTEN INEFFECTUAL
AT HITTING MILITARY
AND INDUSTRIAL TARGETS.
BUT BY 1944, WITH FORD CRANKING
OUT A NEW B-24 EVERY HOUR,
THE AMERICAN BOMBERS
ARE SUCCESSFULLY TARGETING
HITLER'S FACTORIES
AND FUEL SUPPLIES
AND HELPING TURN THE WAR
IN THE ALLIES' FAVOR.
BUT THE CARNAGE AMONG
FLIGHT CREWS IS HORRENDOUS.
IN '43, WE LOST
OVER 3,000 PLANES.
'44, WE LOSE
OVER 11,000 PLANES.
WILLIAM BELIEVES
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
MORAN WAS KILLED
OVER GERMANY.
FLYING DAYLIGHT RAIDS
MADE THE BOMBERS EASY PREY
FOR GERMAN FIGHTER PLANES
AND ANTI-AIRCRAFT GUNS.
IF YOU WERE FLYING
WITH BRITISH BOMBER COMMAND,
YOU HAD A 65% CHANCE
OF BEING A CASUALTY.
IF YOU'RE FLYING IN
THE AMERICAN 8th AIR FORCE,
YOU'VE GOT A 40% TO 60% CHANCE
OF BEING A CASUALTY.
IF YOU'RE LUCKY ENOUGH TO BE
IN THAT KAMIKAZE SQUADRON,
YOU'VE ONLY GOT A 53% CHANCE
OF BEING A CASUALTY.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
WHILE LOGISTICS PROBLEMS
OFTEN KEPT JAPANESE KAMIKAZE
SQUADRONS GROUNDED,
IN EUROPE,
THE BIG ALLIED BOMBERS
WERE SEEING COMBAT
ALMOST DAILY.
SO A KAMIKAZE PILOT
WHO'S SUPPOSED TO KILL HIMSELF
STOOD A BETTER CHANCE
OF SURVIVING
THAN A B-24 BOMBER PILOT?
HARD TO BELIEVE,
ISN'T IT?
WILLIAM SAYS THE OFTEN REMOTE,
MATTER-OF-FACT LANGUAGE
IN SUCH WARTIME WRITING
WAS A WAY OF WALLING OFF
OR ESCAPING
THE HORROR
OF EVERYDAY LIFE.
I THINK IT'S NOT ONLY TYPICAL,
IT'S NECESSARY.
THEY CAN'T BROOD
ABOUT IT.
IT'S GOING TO INTERFERE
WITH THEIR OWN PERFORMANCE,
IT'S GOING TO DEPRESS THEM.
THE WRITING IS A FORM
OF SELF-DEFENSE.
WHAT'S UNUSUAL
ABOUT THE DIARY YOU HAVE
IS THE ROMANTIC ASPECT
OF IT.
I DON'T KNOW ANY OTHER DIARY
THAT I'VE SEEN
WHERE SOMEBODY'S REFERRING
TO HIS WIFE AS "ANGEL."
AND WE HAVE LOTS OF LETTERS
WHERE IT SAYS, "HELLO, HONEY,"
OR SOMETHING OF THAT SORT,
BUT NOT IN THE DIARIES.
THANKS VERY MUCH
FOR SHARING THIS WITH ME.
THANK YOU FOR LETTING ME
SEE THIS.
THIS IS A VERY SPECIAL
DOCUMENT.
I STILL DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHY
BILL MORAN STOPPED WRITING
IN THE JOURNAL,
BUT MY OFFICE
HAS BEEN ABLE
TO TRACK DOWN
HIS MILITARY RECORDS,
AND THEY'VE SENT THEM
TO ME AT THE LIBRARY.
IT'S SOBERING NEWS.
ON OCTOBER 31, 1944,
BILL MORAN WAS FLYING
WITH PILOT EDWARD SPEERS
AND SIX OTHER MEN
WHEN THEIR PLANE DISAPPEARED.
THIS REPORT
OF AIRCRAFT ACCIDENT
OR MISSING AIRCRAFT REPORT
CONFIRMS THAT MORAN WAS KILLED
IN SOME SORT OF
A TRAINING ACCIDENT.
THEY'RE NOT CLEAR EXACTLY
WHAT HAPPENED.
HE TOOK OFF
IN THE FORMATION.
AFTER HE TOOK OFF,
NOBODY ELSE IN THE AIRCRAFT
FORMATION EVER SAW HIM AGAIN.
THE WRECKAGE AND MORAN'S BODY
ARE NEVER FOUND.
THIS TOOK PLACE TWO DAYS AFTER
THE LAST ENTRY IN HIS DIARY.
MARY JAYNE WAS SEVEN MONTHS
PREGNANT WHEN BILL DIED.
IF I'M GOING TO HELP JIM RETURN
THE JOURNAL TO BILL'S FAMILY,
I'M GOING TO NEED HELP
TRACKING DOWN HIS DESCENDANTS.
MY OFFICE HAS LOCATED
JACK PELTON,
ONE OF MORAN'S BUDDIES
MENTIONED IN THE DIARY.
HEY, JACK.
HEY, WES.
JACK AGREES TO MEET ME
AT THE AMERICAN AERO SERVICES
HANGAR IN FLORIDA,
WHERE THE COLLINGS FOUNDATION
MAINTAINS A B-24 BOMBER.
BOY, THIS IS QUITE A PIECE
OF MACHINERY, ISN'T IT?
OH, IT REALLY IS,
IT'S A WONDERFUL AIRPLANE.
AND YOU WERE A PILOT
OF ONE OF THESE BIRDS.
I WAS A PILOT,
FLEW 32 MISSIONS.
HOW'D YOU LIKE TO GET UP
IN THE COCKPIT?
LOVE TO.
OH, WONDERFUL.
IT'S BEEN MORE THAN 50 YEARS
SINCE JACK'S TAKEN A SEAT
AT THE CONTROLS.
SO WHAT WAS IT LIKE
TO FLY ONE OF THESE BABIES?
IT WAS VERY EXCITING,
REALLY.
JACK TELLS ME
IN ORDER TO ATTACK
HEAVILY DEFENDED TARGETS,
PILOTS LIKE HE
AND BILL MORAN FLEW
AT ALTITUDES
OVER 20,000 FEET,
WHERE TEMPERATURES REACHED
MINUS 30 DEGREES.
SO IT WAS COLD,
YOU'RE WEARING AN OXYGEN MASK.
THERE ARE NO HYDRAULICS
IN THESE STEERING WHEELS.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
A HELL OF A JOB.
IT WAS A STRANGE FEELING.
YOU WERE
IN ANOTHER WORLD.
JACK EXPLAINS THAT
THE LIGHTWEIGHT FRAME
THAT MADE THE B-24
SUCH AN EFFICIENT BOMBER
ALSO MADE IT VULNERABLE
TO ENEMY FIRE.
WE BROUGHT ONE PLANE HOME
WITH 153 HOLES IN IT.
[ machine gun firing ]
BULLETS AND SHELLS
FROM GERMAN FIGHTER PLANES
TORE THROUGH
THE AMERICAN AIRCRAFT
AND HELPED EARN THE B-24
ITS REPUTATION
AS A FLYING COFFIN.
YOU KNOW, I'VE GOT
BILL MORAN'S DIARY HERE.
WHAT KIND OF A GUY
WAS BILL MORAN?
WHAT WAS HE LIKE?
BILL MORAN WAS
A GREAT CO-PILOT,
GREAT SENSE OF HUMOR,
IRISHMAN ALL THE WAY.
JACK HAS A PICTURE
OF BILL AND MARY JAYNE,
BILL'S PREGNANT WIFE,
TAKEN RIGHT BEFORE
THE AIRMAN LEFT THE STATES.
SO THAT'S BILL.
BILL.
THAT'S MARY JAYNE.
AND LOOK AT THEM
HOLDING HANDS THERE.
I'D RECOGNIZE YOU
ANYWHERE.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU GUYS
ARE HAVING A LOT OF FUN.
YEAH, WE DID,
HAD A GREAT EVENING.
LAST TIME WE SAW OUR WIVES
FOR A YEAR.
ONE MORE QUESTION:
WHERE WAS BILL MORAN FROM?
PITTSBURGH, PENNSYLVANIA.
MARY JAYNE WAS FROM THERE,
TOO, THEN?
YES, SHE WAS.
WHAT EVER HAPPENED TO
MARY JAYNE, DO YOU KNOW?
I DON'T KNOW.
I TRIED TO FIND HER
WHEN I GOT BACK IN THE STATES,
COULD NOT.
ONE TIME WHEN I WAS
ON BUSINESS IN PITTSBURGH,
I HEARD SHE WAS THERE,
BUT I STILL COULDN'T
TRACK HER DOWN.
SO I'M BACK
AT THE LIBRARY
TO SEARCH THROUGH
GENEALOGICAL RECORDS.
AT FIRST, I DRAW A BLANK
LOOKING FOR MARY JAYNE.
MAYBE I CAN GET INFORMATION
FROM ANOTHER FAMILY MEMBER.
I FINALLY GET A BREAK
WITH THE SOCIAL SECURITY
DEATH INDEX
FOR BILL'S MOTHER VERONICA.
BINGO, HERE SHE IS.
SHE DIED IN MARCH 1967
IN MIAMI, FLORIDA.
HER OBITUARY
EVENTUALLY LEADS US
TO THE NAMES OF TWO
OF BILL'S SURVIVING SISTERS:
ADELAIDE YOUNG
AND JEANIE KIMBROW
OF SEBRING, FLORIDA.
IF THERE'S A LOCAL LISTING,
MAYBE WE'RE IN BUSINESS.
IT TAKES A WHILE,
BUT EVENTUALLY I GET LUCKY.
ADELAIDE YOUNG,
THERE'S HER PHONE NUMBER,
ADDRESS,
BORN AUGUST 1930.
IT'S GOT TO BE HER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'VE FOUND
A LIVING RELATIVE.
HELLO, MRS. YOUNG?
ADELAIDE IS EXCITED
BY NEWS OF THE DIARY,
AND WE MAKE PLANS
TO MEET.
YOU KNOW WHY
I'VE COME TO SEE YOU.
YES.
I HAVE A DIARY THAT WAS WRITTEN
BY YOUR BROTHER.
OH, "MY LIFE
IN THE SERVICE."
DO YOU RECOGNIZE
THAT HANDWRITING?
OH, OF COURSE.
IT'S THE CONSTANT REFERENCES
TO BILL'S WIFE
THAT CATCH ADELAIDE'S EYE.
HE ALWAYS SPEAKS OF HER
IN SUCH A GENTLE WAY.
YOU GET THE SENSE THAT
THEY WERE REALLY IN LOVE.
OH, FROM THE TIME
THEY MET.
ADELAIDE WAS 14
WHEN HER BROTHER DIED.
THE TELEGRAM WAS LAYING
ON THE DINING ROOM TABLE,
AND WE KEPT SAYING, "THEY'LL
FIND HIM, THEY'LL FIND HIM.
SOMEDAY THEY'LL FIND HIM."
THERE WAS NEVER ANY
MEMORIAL SERVICE OR ANYTHING
BECAUSE "SOMEDAY
THEY'LL FIND HIM."
AT FIRST THE VERY PREGNANT
MARY JAYNE
WASN'T EVEN TOLD
HER HUSBAND WAS MISSING.
SHE LEARNED BILL
HAD BEEN KILLED
FROM A FRIEND
WHO VISITED HER
RIGHT AFTER SHE'D GIVEN BIRTH
TO THEIR DAUGHTER.
SHE WAS INCONSOLABLE.
SHE WAS JUST
UNBELIEVABLY IN GRIEF.
MARY JAYNE DIED ROUGHLY
20 YEARS AFTER HER HUSBAND,
BUT WHAT ADELAIDE
REVEALED NEXT
WILL BE EXTRAORDINARY NEWS
FOR JIM.
THIS HAS BEEN
AN INCREDIBLE STORY FOR ME.
I TELL JIM ABOUT SOME OF
THE THINGS I'VE LEARNED
WHILE WORKING
ON BILL'S DIARY.
I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU, THOUGH,
THAT I HAVE SOME BAD NEWS.
I LET JIM KNOW THAT BILL MORAN
DIED IN A TRAINING MISSION
AND HIS WIFE PASSED AWAY
OVER 40 YEARS AGO,
BUT THE STORY
DOESN'T END THERE.
THERE'S SOMEONE I DO
WANT YOU TO MEET,
SO IF YOU WANT TO FOLLOW ME,
WE'LL GO MEET THAT PERSON.
I'D LIKE TO DO THAT.
ADELAIDE TOLD ME
THAT THE BABY
THAT BILL WAS
SO EAGERLY EXPECTING
WAS BORN 32 DAYS
AFTER HE DIED.
HER NAME WAS JANIE.
SHE'S MARRIED.
SHE HAS TWO CHILDREN
AND FOUR GRANDCHILDREN.
BILL MORAN WOULD HAVE BEEN
A GREAT-GRANDFATHER.
HEY, GUYS.
HI.
I WANT YOU TO MEET SOMEBODY,
JIM.
THIS IS JIM CHAPMAN.
THIS IS CHAPPY'S SON.
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
THIS IS ADELAIDE YOUNG.
THIS IS BILL'S SISTER.
I REMEMBER HIM
TALKING ABOUT --
OH, HI, ADELAIDE.
HE TALKED ABOUT BILL CHAPMAN
ALL THE TIME.
OH, IT'S SO NICE
TO MEET YOU.
OH, I'M SO GLAD
AND THIS IS BILL'S DAUGHTER,
JANIE.
HI, JIM,
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
THANK YOU FOR TAKING CARE
OF THE JOURNAL.
I'M SO GLAD
TO HAVE FOUND YOU.
THANKS TO JIM,
BILL MORAN'S THOUGHTS
ARE NOW FINALLY GOING HOME
TO THE DAUGHTER
HE NEVER KNEW.
I JUST FEEL LIKE I KNOW
SO MUCH ABOUT YOU ALREADY.
[ clears throat ]
EXCUSE ME.
SORRY.
THE DIARY'S BEEN IN OUR FAMILY
FOR 63 YEARS.
WHAT WAS SO FASCINATING
WAS READING IN THE DIARY
ABOUT YOUR MOTHER
CARRYING YOU
AND YOUR DAD BEING
SO HAPPY AND EXCITED
ABOUT YOUR MOM
BEING PREGNANT.
IN THE DIARY ITSELF,
IT JUST COMES THROUGH
THAT HE LOVES YOUR MOTHER
VERY MUCH.
MORAN AND HIS FELLOW PILOTS
HAD HELPED DEAL HITLER'S
WAR MACHINE A CRIPPLING BLOW,
AND THEIR CHILDREN
AND CHILDREN'S CHILDREN
WOULD LIVE IN A WORLD
THEY HAD TRANSFORMED.
THIS IS A GLIMPSE
INTO YOUR FATHER'S LIFE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH, JIM,
FOR TREASURING IT
AND TAKING CARE OF IT
FOR ALL THOSE YEARS.
TO HEAR MORE ABOUT
JACK PELTON'S EXPERIENCES
AS A WORLD WAR II
BOMBER PILOT,
VISIT HISTORY DETECTIVES
ON THE WEB AT pbs.org.
Tukufu:
BILL MORAN ALSO WROTE
IN HIS DIARY
ABOUT THE KASSEL MISSION.
IT'S THE BIGGEST SINGLE LOSS
FOR AN AMERICAN BOMBER GROUP
IN THE COUNTRY'S
MILITARY HISTORY.
"WEDNESDAY,
SEPTEMBER 27, 1944.
"BAHN STOPPED IN TO TELL ME
THAT WE LOST 22 OUT OF 35 SHIPS.
"WITHEY, GOLDEN, BOECHER,
ROBINSON, AND REYNOLDS
DIDN'T GET BACK."
JACK PELTON REMEMBERS
THAT DAY WELL.
THEY CALLED ME
FOR THAT MISSION
AND I HAD A PASS
TO GO TO LONDON.
AND I SHOWED THE SERGEANT
MY PASS, AND HE SAID, "OKAY,"
TOOK THE GUY
IN THE NEXT BUNK,
AND HE NEVER CAME HOME.
THIRTY-NINE PLANES
FROM THE 445th BOMB GROUP
SET OUT TO ATTACK A TANK FACTORY
IN KASSEL, GERMANY.
BUT THE LEAD PLANE
MAKES A WRONG TURN,
AND THE 445th
GETS SEPARATED
FROM THE REST
OF THE COMBAT WING.
ALONE OVER ENEMY TERRITORY,
THE LIBERATORS ARE AMBUSHED
BY OVER 100 GERMAN FIGHTERS.
IN LESS THAN FOUR MINUTES,
116 AMERICAN PILOTS ARE DEAD.
SURVIVORS RETURNING TO BASE
RECOUNT THE HORROR.
THE AIR WAS FILLED
WITH BOMBERS BLOWING UP
AND FALLING BOMBER PARTS,
PARACHUTES, AND BODIES,
AND BODY PARTS.
IT WAS A REAL HOLOCAUST.
SOME OF THE GUYS CAME BACK,
THEY WERE ALMOST HYSTERICAL.
THEY COULD HARDLY
CONTAIN THEMSELVES.
THOUGH THE LOSS IS TRAGIC,
THE WAR GOES ON.
THE NEXT DAY, THE MILITARY
SENDS ANOTHER BOMBER GROUP
BACK TO KASSEL
TO FINISH THE JOB.
ALL OF THOSE PLANES
RETURNED SAFELY.
HISTORY DETECTIVES WILL RETURN
IN A MOMENT, BUT FIRST...
Tukufu:
BE A HISTORY DETECTIVE
YOURSELF.
GO TO pbs.org
AND LEARN MORE ABOUT
INVESTIGATIVE TECHNIQUES
OR SUBMIT YOUR OWN MYSTERY
TO THE TEAM.
YOU CAN ALSO FIND OUT MORE
ABOUT TONIGHT'S INVESTIGATIONS
ONLY AT pbs.org.
THIS EPISODE OF HISTORY
DETECTIVES IS AVAILABLE ON DVD.
THE COMPANION BOOK TO
THE PROGRAM IS ALSO AVAILABLE.
TO ORDER,
CALL PBS HOME VIDEO AT...
OR VISIT US ONLINE AT...
Captions by LNS Captioning
Portland, Oregon
www.LNScaptioning.com
Elvis Costello:
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ IT'S JUST LIKE
WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
♪ WATCHIN' THE DETECTIVES ♪
Gwendolyn:
THIS PROGRAM WAS MADE POSSIBLE
BY CONTRIBUTIONS
TO YOUR PBS STATION
FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.
Elyse:
WE'RE THE HISTORY DETECTIVES,
AND WE'RE GOING TO INVESTIGATE
SOME UNTOLD STORIES
FROM AMERICA'S PAST.