w GEICO and
see how much you could
save on homeowners and
condo insurance.
>> Judge Tanya: I feel like
you're trying to take advantage
of these kids.
I do.
>> Judge Patricia: What was your
major?
>> International Relations.
>> Judge Patricia: What's your
major?
>> Communication.
>> Global Health.
>> Psychology.
>> Judge Tanya: I think you
picked the wrong group of
Millennials to mess around with.
>> Announcer: "Hot Bench."
Judge Tanya Acker.
Judge Patricia DiMango.
Judge Michael Corriero.
Three judges.
Three opinions.
One verdict.
Captions paid for by
CBS Television Distribution
>> Sonia: Your Honor, this is
case number 304 -- Phillips,
Washington, Bhatia, Keys,
Brooks, Suleiman, and Moore.
>> Judge Patricia: You just
sound like a law firm.
>> Sonia: Yeah.
[ Laughter ]
>> Judge Patricia: You are?
>> Sidne.
>> Judge Patricia: Sidne.
>> Anika.
>> Judge Patricia: Anika.
>> Rick.
>> Judge Patricia: Rick.
Rick, you and all the ladies.
>> Yep.
[ Laughter ]
>> Amanda.
>> Judge Patricia: Amanda.
>> Ashley.
>> Judge Patricia: Ashley.
>> Kareema.
>> Judge Patricia: Kareema.
Very nice. All right.
Well, the six of you were all
students at the University of
Souther California, and you
rented a five-bedroom home from
the defendant.
You all signed a lease for one
year commencing August 2017,
ending July 31, 2018.
You gave her $7,050 as a
security deposit, and you were
all paying $7,050 a month rent.
Now, in October, apparently,
there was a leak in the ceiling
over the dining room.
The management company came in,
checked out the leak, didn't
hold any of you responsible in
any way, and moved on.
In June, for the first time you
say you met the defendant when
she came to the home, kind of
did a walk-through, walked
around, made no comments about
anything being wrong.
There were no issues, and that
was it.
Then when the lease was up in
the end of July and you were
graduating, you notified the
management company that you'd
all be moving on, and you get an
itemized list thereafter from
the defendant alleging more than
$12,000-worth of damages to the
home, saying that you caused the
leak in the dining room,
that she didn't get proper
notice, 30-day notice, and that
you had also damaged some
property in the dining room,
which was table and a wall unit
or some sort of...
>> It's a TV...
>> Judge Patricia: ...TV center.
You're asking here for $5,000
back from the security deposit.
You say the management company
notified you of the ceiling leak
and you did some investigation,
and after that you realized that
they caused the problem causing
the water to leak into the
downstairs dining room, and all
of this cost you $5,000 over and
above the $7,050 that you kept
from them.
And so you have a counterclaim
for that money, 'cause you also
needed to repair the damaged
property and remove some of
their property.
So, let me just ask you one
question, Ms. Moore.
Can you please give us any
evidence of what the damage was
caused by?
>> I can.
>> Judge Patricia: And why would
you wait until they left to tell
them that they caused the
damage?
Why wouldn't you have notified
them immediately?
>> Because that's when the money
comes out from security deposit.
>> Judge Patricia: But you would
still have to put them on notice
that there was something that
they did.
They were under the impression
that everything was fine.
>> The security deposit is what
it's for -- the money comes out
of that, and it's very clear
from the reports from the
management company that they
could not find the leak, and
then we found that leak that
they did not close the curtains.
>> Judge Patricia: Well, so then
you must have had damage in the
bathroom to show that.
Is that correct?
You had damage on the bathroom
floor?
>> No.
>> Judge Patricia: So there was
no visible damage?
>> So, the water was leaking
through the ceiling into the
living room.
>> Judge Patricia: You had
this...
>> It was on the 3rd of August.
Then it was in October.
>> Judge Patricia: So, wait a
minute.
On the 3rd of August -- They
moved in August 1st.
>> August 30th. 30th.
>> Judge Patricia: You're saying
that 30 days later, there was
leak?
>> There was a leak.
Water was coming down from the
ceiling.
>> Judge Patricia: So, now, this
is my point -- why would you not
tell them, "Listen, there's a
leak, you know, what's going on"
so that they could stop doing
it?
>> They were told, and if you
look, there was no more --
>> Judge Patricia: Who told
them?
You didn't tell them, correct?
>> The management company told
them.
>> Judge Patricia: But you don't
that 'cause you were not there.
>> But April says she told them.
>> Judge Patricia: Well, that's
hearsay.
Okay, thank you for a second.
Okay, Amanda.
>> I'll defer to Sidne.
She has the evidence.
>> We have correspondence with
the management company saying
that we were not responsible for
the leak.
>> Judge Patricia: Ah, let us
see that, please.
This the same company that she
said told you that you did,
except this is in writing.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I can elaborate a little bit.
There are several e-mails you'll
see.
I'm not sure what the dates are
on those orders that she gave
you, but we have several
correspondence, and it's
following up, actually, because
they had the plumber come
several days.
So, the first one says, "We're
gonna come check it out.
We think that it might be
because of this improper shower
curtain use."
Then you'll see another e-mail
that says, "We could not find a
leak."
>> Judge Patricia: I saw one
that said, "We can't find the
leak.
We're gonna fill up the tub."
>> Yes, and then there's a
second e-mail from a couple days
later that says, "We reviewed
it.
We filled up the tubs.
We couldn't find a leak."
>> Judge Patricia: "We ran the
water in the bathrooms located
above the dining room.
We do not see any water leak and
everything is dry.
Please keep an eye out if the
pipes and drains are leaking."
That's from her plumber.
Is that correct?
>> That's from the management
company.
>> Judge Patricia: What else are
you saying they did?
>> [Indistinct] about the leak.
>> Judge Patricia: Ma'am, what
other damages besides the leak
are you saying they caused to
your home?
>> This is the dining table.
This is the dining room, and
this.
>> Judge Patricia: Where is the
list that you sent them, ma'am?
>> We have it.
>> Judge Patricia: I'll take the
list from each of you.
We're starting to notice that
things come up differently from
each side.
>> We've attached her list into
our dispute letter that we
e-mailed her and sent her a hard
copy of.
And then she --
>> Judge Patricia: Let's see
that list.
"Damage to the living room,
improper closing of the shower
curtain caused the leak."
You're charging them $2,500 for
that.
And repairing damage to the
coffee table, dining room table,
entertainment center.
That's something about $450.
So, this is this here -- what
you're talking about the damage?
>> And that was caused by --
>> Judge Patricia: Ladies, was
this damage there when you first
moved in?
It's a discoloration.
Yes, Kareem?
>> Kareema, yes.
There was no damage beyond
normal wear and tear to any of
the furniture.
>> Judge Patricia: Are you a
girl studying law?
[ Laughter ]
Normal wear and tear.
Very good.
>> Yeah, Southland Management
stated in the lease and also in
person when we would ask them
about small things, they said,
"It's normal wear and tear.
It's covered. It's fine."
>> Judge Patricia: It could be,
but she's pointing out something
that looks like it's totally
discolored.
>> I do not personally see
anything on this photo, but I
know the table itself was a
multi-shaded wood color, so I'm
not sure if that's what she's
speaking of.
>> Judge Patricia: So, we'll
have to see a photograph of that
if you have that.
Painting.
You're charging them for the
painting of your apartment after
they lived there for a year?
Were they writing their studies
on the wall?
I mean, what was required?
>> It's amortization schedule,
which is in the lease.
I'm not --
>> Judge Patricia: Did you all
sign a lease that had an
amortization?
You know what?
Can you please pass the lease
up?
So, you agreed that she would
amortize certain things and
pay...?
>> We have the lease.
Also in the lease, marked, is
the 30-day notice, which we
agreed to prior to signing the
lease.
>> Announcer: "Hot Bench"
continues in a moment.
>> Judge Michael: You were aware
that they were leaving.
>> I had no written notice from
them.
>> It says, "This is the 30-day
notice."
>> Judge Michael: I assume each
of you read the lease.
>> We did.
>> Judge Michael: Did you read
the lease?
[ Laughter ]
>> Announcer: Closed caption is
provided by...
You don't get $200
when you switch out
an old car part.
But you do when you switch
to Jackson Hewitt.
At Jackson Hewitt we help
lots of people like you.
That's why you get $200
when you leave your old
tax service for us.
So switch to Jackson Hewitt
today and get $200.
♪♪
>> Announcer: Three judges.
Three opinions.
One verdict.
"Hot Bench."
Former roommates Sidne Phillips,
Anika Washington, Rick Bhatia,
Amanda Keys, Ashley Brooks, and
Kareema Suleiman say former
landlord Lara Moore is
wrongfully withholding their
security deposit.
Lara is countersuing for
property damage and rent.
>> Judge Patricia: You're
charging them $7,000 for failing
to give you 30-day notice when
my understanding of this lease
was that it was up July 31st?
The lease was over.
>> Yeah, but they were supposed
to serve the 30-days notice.
>> Judge Patricia: No, I mean, I
don't see why they would need to
give you notice that they were
leaving when they weren't
staying and the lease was up.
>> They were supposed to serve
this notice in writing.
>> Judge Patricia: "You are
hereby notified tenancy shall
end on July 31st, and we will
deliver possession of the
premises to you on or
before that date."
>> So, this was give for their
convenience within the lease, so
they were supposed to serve it.
>> Judge Patricia: In any event,
where does the $7,000 come from?
>> That's the monthly rent for
not giving the 30-days notice.
>> Judge Patricia: Their lease
expired.
>> If they didn't give me
notice, I couldn't kick them
out --
>> Judge Patricia: It doesn't
say that this converts to a
month-to-month lease after the
fact.
Do you see?
>> Judge Tanya: No, it says
right there, "The lease shall
terminate without further
notice."
>> Judge Patricia: That's it.
That's it.
You drafted this.
They read it. They signed it.
They were out. Done.
August 3rd was the first time
you had the notice of the leak?
>> I believe it was August 30th.
>> Judge Patricia: Did you rent
before them?
>> Yes, I did.
There was never any leak.
>> Judge Patricia: To other
students?
>> Other students.
>> Judge Patricia: Yes?
>> I aim to clarify, and because
I believe that you all should
know, so, Kareema and I were
previous tenants as well.
And I understand that we should
obviously give this context.
So, essentially, Kareema and I
first moved in in August of
2016 with five other roommates.
They all graduated, and I will
note that we signed an original
lease with a different
management company, LAPMG.
About three months in, we were
notified that there was a change
of management to Southland for
the duration of that one-year
lease.
Basically, there was the leak.
The leak occurred while we were
there.
I had called our property
manager.
I said, "Look, there's a leak.
I don't know what to do."
That's the reason I don't have
e-mail documentation of this.
They came over.
They looked at it.
They said, "Okay, we're gonna
call out a plumber."
That is why the August 3rd
happened.
>> Judge Patricia: What was your
major?
>> International Relations.
>> Judge Patricia: What's your
major?
>> Communication.
>> Judge Patricia: Yours?
>> International Relations.
>> Judge Patricia: Sir?
>> Psychology.
>> Judge Patricia: Oh, we need
you.
[ Laughter ]
You?
>> Global Health Pre-Pharmacy.
>> Judge Patricia: And you?
>> Theatre.
>> Judge Patricia: Very nice.
Very nice, all of you.
Very well-poised.
Judge Corriero?
>> Judge Michael: I assume each
of you read the lease, right?
>> We did.
>> Judge Patricia: Look at all
the heads at once.
>> Judge Michael: Yes.
They're good.
So, you actually gave the
defendant a notice that you were
leaving, did you not?
>> We did.
>> Judge Michael: You did text,
right?
>> We text.
>> Judge Michael: You have a
copy of the text?
>> We do.
>> Judge Michael: Did you get
it?
>> The 24th of July I got it.
>> Judge Michael: When did you
send the text?
>> I have the text for us giving
her our new addresses to send
the security deposit.
We also do have proof, though,
of her showing the house to
other tenants from earlier,
so they knew that we were not
staying in the house.
>> Judge Michael: You were aware
that they were leaving, were you
not?
>> I asked Southland, and they
said they had no written notice
from them.
>> Judge Michael: When did you
send the text?
>> I'm not exactly sure which
one.
>> Sorry to interrupt, but I
think that in the lease, there's
a page that we flagged that has
a reference to the 30-day
notice.
I'm not entirely sure if that is
what the defendant is also
referencing.
We signed this back in August
2017.
It says that this is the 30-day
notice.
There's no reason that we
would've know to provide another
one after we signed the lease a
year in advance that already had
a 30-day notice built in.
>> Judge Michael: You didn't
have to because it was an
either/or situation.
Did you understand that?
Did you read the lease?
[ Laughter ]
>> I was told by the
management --
>> Judge Michael: That's not
what I asked you.
I didn't ask you that.
>> I didn't ready that point, I
must say.
>> Judge Michael: Ah, okay.
>> Announcer: "Hot Bench"
continues in a moment.
>> Judge Tanya: I think that
your case is a strategic attempt
to extort $7,000 out of them.
>> That's the monthly rent.
>> Judge Tanya: I think you
picked the wrong group of
Millennials to mess around with.
[ Laughter ]
I was on the fence about
changing
from a manual to an electric
toothbrush.
But my hygienist said going
electric
could lead to way cleaner teeth.
She said, get the one inspired
by dentists,
with a round brush head.
Go Pro with Oral-B. Oral-B's
gentle rounded brush head
removes more plaque along the
gum line.
For cleaner teeth and healthier
gums.
And unlike Sonicare, Oral-B
is the first electric toothbrush
brand
accepted by the ADA
for its effectiveness and
safety.
What an amazing clean!
I'll only use an Oral-B!
Oral-B.
Brush like a pro.
>> Announcer: Three judges.
Three opinions.
One verdict.
"Hot Bench."
Sidne Phillips,
Anika Washington, Rick Bhatia,
Amanda Keys, Ashley Brooks, and
Kareema Suleiman have accused
their former landlord,
Lara Moore, of wrongfully
withholding their security
deposit.
Lara has a countersuit for
property damage and rent.
>> Judge Michael: Why do you
believe that they caused the
leak?
>> I'm very passionate about
that, about the leak, because
none of the plumbers could not
find any reason for the leak
from plumbing.
But as soon as they put some
water on the floor, they told
me, it started to drip down.
>> Judge Michael: Who told you
that?
>> The maintenance company I
called --
>> Judge Michael: But that seems
to contradict the text that the
plaintiffs got that they
couldn't find any leaks.
>> I had to get another company.
>> Judge Michael: Do you have a
written document?
>> Yes, I have -- Southland went
three times there.
>> Judge Michael: What does the
document say?
>> That there was a leak --
>> Judge Michael: Does it say
that the leak was caused by
their failure to close the
shower curtain?
>> That's right.
It's over there.
They investigated.
>> Judge Michael: I'd like to
see these plumbers.
>> Yes, it's a professional
management company.
>> Judge Michael: Yes.
>> Judge Patricia: They're very
specific about that.
>> Judge Michael: Did anybody
notify you of that?
>> No.
>> What we gave you were those
e-mails which told us "we
couldn't find any cause of it."
>> Judge Michael: By any
company?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Michael: When did you
get the second opinion?
>> At the same time when the
leak was happening.
>> Judge Michael: In November?
>> No, October.
>> Judge Michael: But you never
mentioned this at all to the
plaintiffs.
>> I am in contact with
I notified Southland.
plaintiffs.
>> Judge Michael: Well, the
I notified Southland.
management didn't notify them
>> Judge Michael: Well, the
that.
management didn't notify them
>> The management notified them.
that.
>> Judge Michael: That's your
>> The management notified them.
assumption.
>> Judge Michael: That's your
>> Yeah.
assumption.
>> Judge Michael: You say now
>> Yeah.
that you want to charge them
>> Judge Michael: You say now
$2,400...
that you want to charge them
>> That's what it cost me.
$2,400...
>> Judge Michael: ...knowing
>> That's what it cost me.
that almost seven months before
>> Judge Michael: ...knowing
they left.
that almost seven months before
>> Isn't that what's done?
they left.
>> Judge Michael: No. It's not.
>> Isn't that what's done?
If you're a landlord, a
>> Judge Michael: No. It's not.
responsible landlord, you want
If you're a landlord, a
to make sure that they are aware
responsible landlord, you want
of what their responsibilities
to make sure that they are aware
are, and if you're accurate
of what their responsibilities
that it was because of something
are, and if you're accurate
that they were doing, you would
that it was because of something
want to tell them that, wouldn't
that they were doing, you would
you?
want to tell them that, wouldn't
>> But April said she told them.
you?
>> Judge Michael: Well, April
>> But April said she told them.
should be here with you, then,
>> Judge Michael: Well, April
because it's hearsay.
should be here with you, then,
Did April tell you anything?
because it's hearsay.
>> No one told us that we need
Did April tell you anything?
to close the shower curtains to
>> No one told us that we need
stop the leak.
to close the shower curtains to
>> Judge Michael: Okay.
stop the leak.
Thank you very much.
>> Judge Michael: Okay.
[ Laughter ]
Thank you very much.
>> Judge Tanya: Ms. Moore, I
[ Laughter ]
think you picked the wrong group
>> Judge Tanya: Ms. Moore, I
of Millennials to mess around
think you picked the wrong group
with.
of Millennials to mess around
[ Laughter ]
with.
Let's just start with this rent
[ Laughter ]
claim.
Let's just start with this rent
I think it's a frivolous
claim.
bad-faith claim.
I think it's a frivolous
If we were sitting in a
bad-faith claim.
different court, I would
If we were sitting in a
sanction you.
different court, I would
I would make you pay money for
sanction you.
bringing up a claim that is
I would make you pay money for
plainly contradicted by the
bringing up a claim that is
documents.
plainly contradicted by the
Your lease says, "The lease
documents.
shall terminate without further
Your lease says, "The lease
notice."
shall terminate without further
How dare you sue them for $7,000
notice."
for not giving you something
How dare you sue them for $7,000
they weren't obligated to do.
for not giving you something
I mean, that's outrageous.
they weren't obligated to do.
I saw in your itemized damages
I mean, that's outrageous.
you want us to give you money to
I saw in your itemized damages
repaint the whole home.
you want us to give you money to
>> That's in the lease.
repaint the whole home.
>> Judge Tanya: Show me.
>> That's in the lease.
Show me.
>> Judge Tanya: Show me.
>> That's in the lease.
Show me.
>> Judge Tanya: Because it's
>> That's in the lease.
interesting to me that you read
>> Judge Tanya: Because it's
parts of your lease but not
interesting to me that you read
other parts of your lease.
parts of your lease but not
I'm gonna hand you this back,
other parts of your lease.
and you show me where it is
I'm gonna hand you this back,
they're liable to pay you to
and you show me where it is
repaint the whole apartment.
they're liable to pay you to
I got to tell you, I don't see
repaint the whole apartment.
these thousands of dollars, and
I got to tell you, I don't see
I think that part of the
these thousands of dollars, and
defendant's claim is so
I think that part of the
offensive I'd like to just
defendant's claim is so
dismiss the whole thing.
offensive I'd like to just
It's absurd of her to try and
dismiss the whole thing.
seek $7,000 when her lease says
It's absurd of her to try and
you didn't have to do that.
seek $7,000 when her lease says
That's a waste of everybody's
you didn't have to do that.
time.
That's a waste of everybody's
>> Your Honors, I'll also say
time.
that because we moved in after
>> Your Honors, I'll also say
another group, none of the
that because we moved in after
furniture was replaced.
another group, none of the
>> And it was not repainted.
furniture was replaced.
>> Judge Tanya: So, did you
>> And it was not repainted.
repaint after the last tenancy?
>> Judge Tanya: So, did you
>> The apartment was
repaint after the last tenancy?
repainted --
>> The apartment was
>> Judge Tanya: It's a yes or
repainted --
no.
>> Judge Tanya: It's a yes or
Did you paint after the last
no.
tenancy?
Did you paint after the last
>> In '16?
tenancy?
>> Judge Tanya: Yeah, before
>> In '16?
they moved in.
>> Judge Tanya: Yeah, before
>> I don't remember that.
they moved in.
>> Judge Tanya: You remember
>> I don't remember that.
that she didn't, and now you
>> Judge Tanya: You remember
want another $3,000 for
that she didn't, and now you
repainting the place.
want another $3,000 for
You know what?
repainting the place.
I got to tell you, Ms. Moore, I
You know what?
feel like you're trying to take
I got to tell you, Ms. Moore, I
advantage of these kids.
feel like you're trying to take
I do.
advantage of these kids.
I think that your case is a
I do.
strategic attempt to take
I think that your case is a
advantage of these students.
strategic attempt to take
You want to try to extort $7,000
advantage of these students.
out of them, which your lease
You want to try to extort $7,000
says you're not even entitled
out of them, which your lease
to, and then you want to try to
says you're not even entitled
get another $5,000-worth of
to, and then you want to try to
damages because of some water
get another $5,000-worth of
marks on your table.
damages because of some water
You should be ashamed of trying
marks on your table.
to take advantage of these kids
You should be ashamed of trying
like this.
to take advantage of these kids
I actually don't have any other
like this.
questions for you.
I actually don't have any other
>> Judge Patricia: We're gonna
questions for you.
retire to deliberate.
>> Judge Patricia: We're gonna
Thank you.
retire to deliberate.
>> Sonia: This courtroom is now
Thank you.
in recess.
>> Sonia: This courtroom is now
♪♪
in recess.
>> Judge Patricia: All right, so
♪♪
they're both suing for $5,000.
>> Judge Patricia: All right, so
The plaintiffs are suing because
they're both suing for $5,000.
they say, "At least give us back
The plaintiffs are suing because
$5,000 'cause that's the court
they say, "At least give us back
maximum 'cause we didn't do any
$5,000 'cause that's the court
of the damages you're talking
maximum 'cause we didn't do any
about."
of the damages you're talking
And the counterclaim is about
about."
"you owe me more because I'm
And the counterclaim is about
keeping your $7,000 and I want
"you owe me more because I'm
$5,000 on top of that for all of
keeping your $7,000 and I want
this extra damage."
$5,000 on top of that for all of
Well, I think the plaintiffs
this extra damage."
prevail and the defendant does
Well, I think the plaintiffs
not.
prevail and the defendant does
Let's look at them
not.
independently.
Let's look at them
We have no proof other than what
independently.
is an out-of-court statement to
We have no proof other than what
say that these plaintiffs
is an out-of-court statement to
actually caused the leak or the
say that these plaintiffs
damages.
actually caused the leak or the
And there's no evidence that
damages.
anything was done in order to
And there's no evidence that
stop it, so that's done for me.
anything was done in order to
>> Judge Michael: And you know
stop it, so that's done for me.
what troubles me?
>> Judge Michael: And you know
If she felt that they were gonna
what troubles me?
be responsible, not telling them
If she felt that they were gonna
for seven months?
be responsible, not telling them
>> Judge Patricia: That's what I
for seven months?
said in the beginning.
>> Judge Patricia: That's what I
>> Judge Tanya: I think it's all
said in the beginning.
ginned up.
>> Judge Tanya: I think it's all
>> Judge Patricia: So, that's
ginned up.
the first thing.
>> Judge Patricia: So, that's
The second thing is with regard
the first thing.
to the damage.
The second thing is with regard
Since I don't believe that they
to the damage.
caused the leak, there's no
Since I don't believe that they
reason to hold them responsible
caused the leak, there's no
for the leak damages that are on
reason to hold them responsible
the property, and there's no
for the leak damages that are on
other damage there.
the property, and there's no
With regard to the $7,000 that's
other damage there.
she's charging them because they
With regard to the $7,000 that's
didn't give her 30-days notice
she's charging them because they
that they were leaving, her own
didn't give her 30-days notice
lease clearly points out that it
that they were leaving, her own
would've expired.
lease clearly points out that it
It ends automatically.
would've expired.
It's a lease. It's over.
It ends automatically.
There was no agreement to stay
It's a lease. It's over.
on.
There was no agreement to stay
She just falsified, basically,
on.
these charges, and you love
She just falsified, basically,
these frivolous lawsuits.
these charges, and you love
>> Judge Tanya: Oh, my favorite.
these frivolous lawsuits.
>> Judge Patricia: So, I mean,
>> Judge Tanya: Oh, my favorite.
this is as frivolous as it gets.
>> Judge Patricia: So, I mean,
>> Judge Tanya: I think her
this is as frivolous as it gets.
position is entirely
>> Judge Tanya: I think her
preposterous.
position is entirely
>> Judge Patricia: It's awful.
preposterous.
>> Judge Tanya: Shame on her.
>> Judge Patricia: It's awful.
>> Judge Patricia: What a nice
>> Judge Tanya: Shame on her.
group of young kids.
>> Judge Patricia: What a nice
All right, well, I'm ready to
group of young kids.
dismiss the counterclaim and
All right, well, I'm ready to
give them their $5,000 back.
dismiss the counterclaim and
>> Judge Tanya: I'm right there
give them their $5,000 back.
with you.
>> Judge Tanya: I'm right there
>> Judge Michael: I'm with you.
with you.
>> Judge Patricia: All right.
>> Judge Michael: I'm with you.
♪♪
>> Judge Patricia: All right.
>> Announcer: "Hot Bench"
♪♪
continues in a moment.
>> Announcer: "Hot Bench"
ClThe best... in so many ways...
Which cage free eggs taste
more delicious,
with better nutrition, too?
Only Eggland's Best.
Better taste, better
nutrition, better eggs.
My BLT gave me the
heartburn blues.
But Rolaids® made it all fine.
For heartburn, Rolaids starts
working as fast as now.
Get your Groove Back™
with Rolaids®.
>> Announcer: Three judges.
Three opinions.
One verdict.
"Hot Bench."
With uncontrolled
moderate-to-severe eczema,
or atopic dermatitis,
you never know how
your skin will look.
And it can feel like
no matter what you do,
you're always itching.
But even though you see and
feel eczema on your skin,
an overly sensitive
immune system
deep WITHIN your skin
could be the cause.
So help heal your skin
from within.
With DUPIXENT.
DUPIXENT is not a steroid,
and it continuously
treats your eczema
even when you can't see it.
At 16 weeks,
more than 1 in 3 patients saw
clear or almost clear skin,
and patients saw a significant
reduction in itch.
Do not use if you are
allergic to DUPIXENT.
Serious allergic
reactions can occur,
including anaphylaxis,
a severe reaction.
Tell your doctor if you have new
or worsening eye problems,
including eye pain or
changes in vision.
If you are taking asthma
medicines,
do not change or stop
your asthma medicine
without talking
to your doctor.
Help heal your
skin from within.
Ask your eczema specialist
about DUPIXENT.
>> Judge Patricia: We are
unanimous about a lot of things
here.
First of all, we fully believe
that you are all an amazing
example of what our future's
going to be like if we have many
young people like you who have
not evidenced to us any sense of
entitlement, who have been
respectful not only of us but of
other people's property and of
themselves, and it's amazing to
see that in here, 'cause we
don't always get the opportunity
to see the better part of life.
On the other hand, we have some
issues with regard to the
legalities of your position,
ma'am, or your defense in this
case.
So, let's put it out there --
two cases.
$5,000 for you.
You want your money back.
She's wrongfully withheld your
security deposit and you've
challenged that.
You want $5,000 more.
You say they caused
$12,000-worth of damage, and
what you have submitted, one, in
evidence of the damage to the
leaky roof was hearsay.
These are not medical records.
They're not exempt from
anything.
It's a hand-written note saying
that some shower curtain being
open caused the leak.
So, we have no evidence, indeed,
that it was these six
individuals that caused the
leak.
So as to the damage for those
repairs, we're not going to
charge them with that.
That being said, we can't
attribute the leak or any spots
on the table that might have
been caused by that leak to them
as well, and everything else
would've been normal wear and
tear.
And with regard to the $7,000
that you're asking for because
they did not give you notice
pursuant to a lease that you
drafted, you gave them, and they
signed that said "no notice
necessary, this ends on July
31st," well, we kind of took the
lease at its word, not yours,
and so we are dismissing your
counterclaim for damages over
and above the $7,000 you've
already kept, and we are going
to award you the $5,000 that
you're requesting as a return of
your security deposit.
Good luck to all of you.
You're a wonderful group.
We have a unanimous verdict in
your favor for $5,000.
Thank you.
>> Sonia: This courtroom is now
in recess.
>> Announcer: "Hot Bench"
continues in a moment.
And on the next "Hot Bench"...
>> I can't say I'm surprised,
however, I am very relieved.
>> It's a lesson to me.
I must document it better.
>> We weren't gonna back down.
We knew we deserved it.
>> I should be more hands-on
management.
>> We just have to stand up and
use our education to fight back.
>> Bad management company took
advantage of me.
>> Fight on!
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
[phone ringing]
Remember the way we
used to do things?
Hey man...
Like connect with friends?
Dig it!
Or get in shape?
Or sell a house
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
[crash]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.