>>> THE LOOK OF LOVE?
LADY GAGA AND BRADLEY COOPER
SIZZLING CHEMISTRY.
>> BREATHTAKING.
>> THE MOMENT EVERYONE IS
TALKING ABOUT.
>> WHAT WAS HIS GIRLFRIEND
THINKING?
>> I FELT SO UNCOMFORTABLE FOR
HIS GIRLFRIEND.
>> AND THEN SPIKE'S FURY.
WHY HE STORMED OUT OF THE
OSCARS.
AND WHAT YOU DIDN'T SEE ON TV.
>> THEN.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO SAY TO
YOUR FANS?
>> HE WAS WORTH $150 MILLION.
SO WHY CAN'T SINGER R. KELLY
POST BAIL?
>> PLUS FIRST PHOTOS.
TOM BRADY AND WIFE GISELLE WITH
THE EMBATTLED OWNER OF THE NEW
ENGLAND PATRIOTS.
AND UX COLLUSIVE FIRST VIDEO.
MIRANDA LAMBERT AND HER NEW
NYPD HUSBAND.
>> HOW IS MARRIAGE FOR YOU
GUYS?
>> THEN.
>> DOG VERSES GODZILLA.
>> THE FAMILY DOG TRAPPED IN A
HOLE BY A TORTOISE NAMED
GODZILLA.
NOW INSIDE EDITION WITH DEBORAH
NORVILLE.
>> THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
THE 91st ACADEMY AWARDS IS
HISTORY AND THE MOST TALKED
ABOUT MOMENT HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH AN OSCAR.
IT WAS THAT DUET BETWEEN LADY
GAGA AND BRADLEY COOPER AS THEY
PERFORMED THE NOMINATED SONG
FROM A STAR IS BORN.
WHILE THE SONG DID WIN AN
OSCAR, ALL THAT HEAT ON STAGE
HAD THE INTERNET SIZZLING.
>> Reporter: IT WAS THE MOST
ANTICIPATED MOMENT OF OSCAR
NIGHT AND HOLY MOLY DID IT
DELIVER.
♪ IN THE SHALLOW WE FALL FROM
THE SHALLOW NOW ♪
>> Reporter: NEWLY SINGLE LADY
GAGA AND BRADLEY COOPER SET THE
STAGE ON FIRE WITH THEIR
ELECTRIFYING CHEMISTRY.
>> THE EYE CONTACT.
THAT TO ME STOLE THE OSCARS.
>> Reporter: NOW EVERYONE IS
ASKING, IS SOMETHING REALLY
GOING ON BETWEEN THEM?
>> I KNOW WHAT ALL OF YOU ARE
THINKING.
>> TALK ABOUT CHEMISTRY.
BREATHTAKING.
>> WHAT IS GOING ON?
>> I THINK THEY ARE EITHER
REALLY ACTORS OR SOMETHING IS
GOING ON.
>> Reporter: THE SIZZLING
PERFORMANCE PRACTICALLY BROKE
THE INTERNET WITH THEIR LOCKED
GEORGIA BECOMING AN INSTANT
MEME.
GET A ROM GOES THIS TWEET.
SHOULD WE LEAVE?
SEEMS THEY WANT TO BE ALONE
GOES ANOTHER.
I'M SORRY BUT IF YOU ARE
BRADLEY'S GIRLFRIEND, AREN'T
YOU SLIGHTLY NERVOUS?
BRADLEY'S GIRLFRIEND WAS
WATCHING IT ALL FROM THE FRONT
ROW.
>> I FELT SO UNCOMFORTABLE FOR
BRADLEY'S GIRLFRIEND.
OH MY GOSH.
>> Reporter: SO WHAT WAS IRENA
THINKING?
MAYBE THIS IS A CLUE.
AFTER THE SIZZLING PERFORMANCE,
SHE WAS SEEN TAKING PART IN THE
STANDING OVATION.
AND IN THIS BEHIND THE SCENES
VIDEO WHEN BRADLEY AND GAGA
WERE TURNED TO THEIR SEATS
DURING A COMMERCIAL BREAK, THEY
GOT A SECOND STANDING O AND
THERE IS IRENA JOINING IN.
BRADLEY GAVE HER A SWEET SMASH
AS GAGA STOOD RIGHT THERE.
GAGA SAD BRADLEY CHOREOGRAPHED
THEIR INTIMATE PERFORMANCE
WHICH BEGAN WITH THE STARS
WALKING ON STAGE WITHOUT ANY
INTRODUCTION.
♪ TELL ME SOMETHING GIRL ♪
>> Reporter: THEY LOCKED EYES
FOR 40 SECONDS AND WITH THAT
BECAME AN OVERNIGHT OSCAR
LEGEND.
>> AFTER THAT PERFORMANCE I
SAID OUTLOUD, THIS IS ONE OF
THOSE MOMENTS THAT IS GOING TO
GO DOWN IN OSCAR HISTORY.
>>  Deborah: MOST OF THE
ACCEPTANCE SPEECHES THIS YEAR
STEERED CLEAR OF POLITICS, BUT
WHEN SPIKE LEE WON HIS FIRST
COMPETITIVE OSCAR EVER, HE MADE
MENTION OF THE 2020 ELECTION
AND ALTHOUGH HE DIDN'T SAY A
NAME, EVERYONE KNEW WHO HE WAS
TALKING ABOUT.
AND TODAY THE PRESIDENT IS
HITTING BACK.
>> GREEN BOOK.
>> Reporter: THE UPSET WINNER
FOR BEST PICTURE IS REALLY
UPSETTING SPIKE LEE.
HE WAS SEEN WAVING HIS ARMS IN
ANGER AND STORMING OUT.
THAT IS HIS EMPTY SEAT AS THE
CAST OF GREEN BOOK GAVE THEIR
ACCEPTANCE SPEECH.
>> THIS IS MY SIXTH GLASS.
>> Reporter: BACKSTAGE HE WAS
DROWNING HIS SORROWS WITH
CHAMPAGNE AND NOT HIDING HIS
FURY.
>> CAN YOU GIVE US YOUR
THOUGHTS ON THAT BEST PICTURE
WIN?
>> LET ME TAKE ANOTHER SIP.
NEXT QUESTION.
>> Reporter: EARLIER IN THE
NIGHT WHEN I CAUGHT UP WITH HIM
ON THE RED CARPET, HE WAS IN
MUCH BETTER SPIRITS.
>> YOU LOOK GREAT.
>> Reporter: AND THEN HIS DREAM
CAME TRUE.
HE WON AN OSCAR FOR BEST
ADAPTIVE SCREEN PLAY FOR
BLACKKKLANSMAN AND LEAP INTO
THE ARMS OF SAMUEL L. JACKSON
BROUGHT DOWN THE THE HOUSE.
HE USED HIS ACCEPTANCE SPEECH
TO TAKE A SWIPE AT PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
>> THE 2020 PRESIDENTIAL
ELECTION IS AROUND THE CORNER.
LET'S ALL MOBILIZE AND ALL BE
ON THE RIGHT SIDE OF HISTORY.
MAKE THE MORAL CHOICE BETWEEN
LOVE VERSES HATE.
LET'S DO THE RIGHT THING.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT IS
HITTING BACK TODAY.
JUST BEFORE LEAVING FOR HIS
SUMMIT IN VIETNAM.
BE NICE IF SPIKE LEE COULD
READNOTES OR BETTER YET NOT
HAVE TO USE NOTES AT ALL.
NO HOST WAS A BREAK WITH
TRADITION.
GONE WAS THE OPENING MONOLOGUE
IN ITS PLACE A ROCK ANTHEM BY
THE SUPER GROUP QUEEN THAT HAD
EVERYONE BUZZING.
♪ WE WILL WE WILL ROCK YOU ♪
>> Reporter: THE MOVIE ABOUT
QUEEN BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY HAD A
BIG NIGHT WITH FOUR WINS
INCLUDING BEST ACTOR RAMI
MALEK.
MALEK HAD A BIG OOPS MOMENT AT
THE END OF THE BROADCAST.
LITERALLY.
HE FELL OFF THE STAGE.
PARAMEDICS WERE CALLED BUT HE
WASN'T SERIOUSLY INJURED.
REGINA KING WAS ENJOYING EVERY
MOMENT OF HER OSCAR NIGHT.
>> REGINA KING.
>> Reporter: HER MOM WAS RIGHT
THERE AS REGINA WON THE FIRST
AWARD OF THE NIGHT.
BEST SUPPORTING ACTRESS.
HER GORGEOUS GOWN CAUGHT IN HER
SHOE BUT CHRIS EVANS PROVED
CHIVALRY ISN'T DEAD AND HE
HELPED HER UP THE STEPS.
>> MOM, I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> Reporter: SO WHAT WAS THE
VERDICT ON THE NO HOST OSCARS?
SOME ON SOCIAL MEDIA CALLED THE
SHOW BORING.
OTHERS THOUGHT IT ALL CAME
TOGETHER.
>> QUITE A SHOW.
MAYBE THEY DIDN'T NEED A HOST
AFTER ALL.
>> Reporter: AND HERE'S WHAT
ELSE YOU DIDN'T SEE ON TV.
THE ACTION AT THE GOVERNOR'S
BALL.
REGINA KING GOT EMOTIONAL WHEN
SHE SAW HER ENGRAVED OSCAR FOR
THE FIRST TIME.
LADY GAGA COZIED UP TO HER
COWRITER FOR BEST ORIGINAL
SONG.
AND RAMI MALEK SCREWED HIS
NEWLY ENGRAVED NAME PLATE ON TO
HIS OSCAR HIMSELF.
>> I THINK THAT IS PRETTY GOOD.
>> Reporter: BEFORE SPRAYING
CHAMPAGNE ALL OVER THE ROOM.
>> AND THAT IS WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU WIN AN OSCAR.
>>  Deborah: AND THERE WAS A
SURPRISE GUEST AT AN OSCAR
PARTY IN BEVERLY HILLS.
NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS OWNER
ROBERT KRAFT WHO STEPPED OUT
THE DAY AFTER HE WAS NAMED IN A
HUGE PROSTITUTION STING.
HE WAS SPOTTED AGAIN THIS
MORNING GIVING US THE FIRST
PHOTOS OF MR. KRAFT WITH HIS
STAR QUARTERBACK TOM BRADY AND
HIS WIFE GISELLE.
>> Reporter: TOM BRADY IS
SHOWING SUPPORT FOR HIS MENTOR
AND BOSS NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS
OWNER ROBERT KRAFT IN THE WAKE
OF HIS PROSTITUTION SCANDAL.
ROBERT KRAFT LOOKING CASUAL IN
ATHLETIC GEAR ARRIVED AT A
PRIVATE AIRPORT.
TOM BRADY WAS ON THE FLIGHT
ALONG WITH HIS WIFE SUPER MODEL
GISELLE.
THE TRIO FLEW IN FROM LOS
ANGELES AFTER KRAFT ATTENDED A
PREOSCAR'S PARTY SATURDAY
NIGHT.
TOM BRADY AND KRAFT EMBRACED
AND THE STAR QUARTERBACK GIVES
KRAFT A KISS ON THE CHEEK
BEFORE PARTING WAYS.
AUTHORITIES SAY KRAFT WAS
CAUGHT IN TWO SEPARATE SEX ACTS
AT THE OR KIDS OF ASIA'S DAY
SPAT IN JUPITER, FLORIDA.
OFFICIALS ANNOUNCED ROBERT
KRAFT WILL NOT BE GIVEN ANY
SPECIAL TREATMENT IN THE
INVESTIGATION.
>> I CAN ASSURE YOU THAT OUR
OFFICE TREATS EVERYONE THE
SAME.
WHETHER YOU HAVE A LOT OF MONEY
OR YOU ARE INDIGENT.
RETREAT ALL THE DEFENDANTS THE
SAME.
NO ONE GETS ANY SPECIAL
JUSTICE.
>> Reporter: THE SPA HAD BEEN
UNDER POLICE SURVEILLANCE IN
CONNECTION TO A INVESTIGATION
INTO A HUMAN TRAFFICKING RING.
>> UNDER THE CIRCUMSTANCES HE
IS NOT LIKELY NOT LOOKING AT
JAIL TIME.
EVEN IF HE IS CONVICT.
HE WILL PROBABLY BE ON
PROBATION.
>> Reporter: BRADY AND KRAFT
ARE CLOSE FRIENDS.
JUST THREE WEEKS AGO THEY
CELEBRATED THEIR LATEST SUPER
BOWL VICTORY.
AND JUDGING BY THE IMAGES,
BRADY IS STANDING BY HIM IN
THIS TIME OF PERSONAL CRISIS.
>>  Deborah: THE NFL'S PERSONAL
CONDUCT POLICY APPLIES TO BOTH
PLAYERS AND OWNERS.
AND TODAY THE LEAGUE SAID IT
WOULD TAKE APPROPRIATE ACTION
AGAINST KRAFT IF NECESSARY.
ROBERT KRAFT MAINTAINS HIS
INNOCENCE.
>>> R. KELLY WAS ONCE ONE OF
THE HIGHEST PAID MUSICIANS IN
AMERICA.
BUT DESPITE EARNING IN EXCESS
OF $100-$150 MILLION ON
HISCARJACKS OF SEX CHARGES HE'S
HAVING TROUBLE COMING UP WITH
$100 NEEDED FOR BOND.
>> Reporter: HE HAS YET TO COME
UP WITH THE $100,000 BAIL.
THE SINGER HAS BEEN BEHIND BARS
SINCE FRIDAY NIGHT AFTER BEING
UNABLE TO BAIL OUT.
R. KELLY'S LAWYER SAYS THE
SINGERS FINANCES ARE A MESS.
>> THIS IS SOMEONE WHO SHOULD
BE WEALTHY AT THIS STAGE IN HIS
CAREER.
AND THROUGH MISMANAGEMENT AND
THROUGH PEOPLE HANGING ON AND
BAD CONTRACTS AND BAD DEALS AND
BAD LEASES LIKE HE HAD ON HIS
STUDIO, HE REALLY DOESN'T HAVE
ANY MONEY AT THIS POINT.
♪ I BELIEVE I CAN FLY ♪
>> Reporter: HE WAS SAID TO
ONCE BE WORTH $150 MILLION.
I SPOKE TO A KELLY ACCUSER THAT
WAS FEATURED IN THE LIFE-TIME
EXPOSE SURVIVING R. KELLY.
HE'S HAVING TROUBLE POSTING
BAIL.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THAT?
>> I HOPE IT'S NOT A TACTIC
FROM HIS LEGAL TEAM TO PRETEND
HE DOESN'T HAVE THE MONEY TO
POST BOND TO GET A LOWER BOND.
>> Reporter: KELLY HAS PLED NOT
GUILTY TO THE CHARGES.
THIS IS COOK COUNTY JAIL IN
CHICAGO WHERE KELLY HAS SPENT
THE LAST THREE NIGHTS.
AND LOOK, R. KELLY'S MUG SHOT
WAS TAKEN IN FRONT OF THE SAME
CINDER BLOCK WALL WHERE EMPIRE
STAR JUSSIE SMOLLETT HAD HIS
MUG SHOT TAKEN THE DAY BEFORE.
THE DING IN THE WALL IS THE
SAME IN BOTH PHOTOS.
>> AND SPEAKING OF JUSSIE
SMOLLETT, IS THIS $3500 CHECK
THE SPOKING GUN OR PROOF OF HIS
INNOCENCE?
THE CHECK WAS WRITTEN BY
SMOLLETT TO THE BODY DIAMOND
BUILDERS THAT TELLS POLICE HE
AND HIS BROTHER WERE PAID TO
STAGE THAT ATTACK.
BUT SMOLLETT CONTENDS IT'S
SIMPLY A CHECK FOR HIS PERSONAL
TRAINER.
HERE'S MORE ON WHAT IS SURE TO
BE A MUCH DEBATED PIECE OF
EVIDENCE IN THE CASE AGAINST
THE ACTOR.
>> Reporter: IT'S A KEY POSE OF
EVIDENCE.
THE CHECK POLICE SAY EMPIRE
STAR JUSSIE SMOLLETT WROTE TO
PAY TWO BROTHERS TO STAGE THE
HOAX.
IT'S FOR $3,500.
PAYABLE TO ABINDOLA.
A BODYBUILDER AND HIS PERSONAL
TRAINER.
THAT IS SAID TO BE JUSSIE
SMOLLETT'S SIGNATURE.
IN THE MEMO LINE HE HAS WRITTEN
FIVE WEEK NUTRITION WORKOUT
PROGRAM.
THE CHECK IS DATED
JANUARY 23rd BUT POLICE SAY IT
WAS WRITTEN JANUARY 27th.
TWO DAYS BEFORE SMOLLETT
CLAIMED HE WAS ATTACKED.
WE CAUGHT UP WITH CHICAGO
POLICE SUPERINTENDENT EDDY
JOHNSON IN NEW YORK AFTER HE
APPEARED ON GOOD MORNING
AMERICA MONDAY.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE CHECK THAT HE
SAYS WAS FOR TRAIN SOMETHING
>> Reporter: TERRANCE HOWARD
THAT PLACE SMOLLETT'S FATHER ON
EMPIRE IS BREAKING HIS SILENCE.
HE POSTED THIS VIDEO OF
SMOLLETT PLAYS WITH HOWARD'S
TWO-YEAR-OLD SON ON A PLANE.
ALONG WITH A MESSAGE, THE
JUSSIE I KNOW COULD NEVER EVEN
CONCEIVE OF SOMETHING SO UGLY.
>> SUCH A SWEET BABY.
>> Reporter: SMOLLETT HAS BEEN
WRITTEN OUT OF THE LAST TWO
EPISODES OF THIS SEASON OF
EMPIRE.
>>  Deborah: SMOLLETT IS DUE
BACK IN COURT MARCH 14th.
IF CONVICTED OF THE CHARGES, HE
COULD FACE UP TO THREE YEARS IN
PRISON.
HE MAINTAINS HIS INNOCENCE.
>>> THE CENSUS BUREAU SAYS
THERE IS 3.5 MILLION COMMUTER
COUPLES.
AND ONE OF THE LATEST WAS JUST
SPOTTED TOGETHER MAKING THE
TRIP TO NEW YORK.
WE HAVE YOUR FIRST LOOK AT
MIRANDA LAMBERT WITH HER NEW
HUSBAND.
>> Reporter: IT'S MIRANDA
LAMBERT AND HER NEW POLICE
OFFICER HUSBAND SEEN FOR THE
FIRST TIME SINCE THEY ANNOUNCED
THEIR WORLD WIND MARRIAGE.
>> HOW IS MARRIAGE FOR YOU
GUYS?
>> Reporter: WE CAUGHT UP WITH
THE NEWLYWEDS AFTER THEY LANDED
IN NEW YORK FOLLOWING AN EARLY
MORNING FLIGHT FROM NASHVILLE.
INSIDE EDITION OBTAINED THESE
EXCLUSIVE PHOTOS SHOWING THEM
DRESSED DOWN IN JACKETS AND
HATS AS THEY WAITED TO BOARD
THE PLANE.
THEY LOOKED HAPPY CARRYING BAGS
AND A PILLOW.
A FELLOW PASSENGER TELLS US
MIRANDA AND 27-YEAR-OLD BRANDON
MCLAUGHLIN AN NYPD COP SAT IN
FIRST CLASS AND GIVEN A
CHAMPAGNE TOAST BY A FLIGHT
ATTENDANT.
WE WERE THERE WHEN THEY LANDED
AND IT'S SAFE TO SAY THEY WERE
NOT TOO HAPPY TO BE RECOGNIZED.
>> IF I SAY SOMETHING WILL YOU
LEAVE?
LIKE THE WORLD SHOULD MINE
THEIR OWN BUSINESS.
>> Reporter: MCLAUGHLIN IS
BELIEVED TO BE GOING BACK TO
WORK AFTER A WEEKEND IN
NASHVILLE.
MIRANDA SURPRISED FANS AT A
CONCERT JOINING FELLOW
COUNTRYSTARS KEITH URBAN AND
DIRKS BENTLEY ON STAGE.
HER FIRST SINCE THE WEDDING.
>> WE'LL BE BACK WITH MORE
INSIDE EDITION AFTER THIS.
>>> NEXT.
>>  Deborah: DOG VERSES
GODZILLA.
>> THE FAMILY DOG TRAPPED IN A
HOLE BY A TORTOISE NAMED
GODZILLA.
>> PLUS J-LO, JENNIFER, EMMA.
OSCAR FASHION HITS AND MISSES.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
My name is
Elaine Barber,
and I'm a
five-year cancer survivor.
Surviving for five years
is a big deal.
I had so many people at CTCA
helping me find a way to go
through the treatments.
The reality of cancer is
not everybody survives.
At CTCA,
they have a huge
celebrate life event.
That was amazing
because the whole day
was about all of the survivors.
I'm excited about my future.
Learn more at
cancercenter.com/Philadelphia.
>>> WHAT'S GOING ON INSIDE THE
NEIGHBORHOOD SPA?
NEXT INSIDE EDITION.
THEY SAY THEY OFFER MASSAGES.
BUT ARE THEY ALSO OFFERING MORE
THAN THAT?
AFTER THE SHOCKING ALLEGATIONS
THAT THE OWNER OF THE NEW
ENGLAND PATRIOTS FOOTBALL TEAM,
INSIDE EDITION INVESTIGATES.
INSIDE YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD SPA.
THEN.
>> GREEN BOOK.
>> CONTROVERSY OVER THE OSCAR
WINNING FILM GREEN BOOK.
NEXT INSIDE EDITION.
>>  Deborah: COLOR, SPARKLE,
BIG BALL GOWNS, THERE WAS
PRETTY MUCH SOMETHING FOR
EVERYONE ON THE OSCAR RED
CARPET.
WE'VE GOT A RUN DOWN OF THIS
YEAR'S FASHION HITS AND MISSES.
>> Reporter: JENNIFER LOPEZ
KNOCKED IT OUT OF THE BALLPARK
IN A MIRRORED GOWN BY TOM FORD.
AT HER SIDE BOYFRIEND AL
EXRODRIGUEZ.
>> THE ACCESSORY WAS AROD.
HE WAS IN ALL WHITE TUXEDO.
>> Reporter: VOGUE MAGAZINE
CALLED THEM THE BEST DRESSED
COUPLE.
HERE'S VICTORIA.
>> DESPITE COLD TEMPERATURES ON
THE RED CARPET, STARS SHINE
BRIGHT DAZZLED IN JEWELS
BRINGING OLD TIME HOLLYWOOD
GLAMOUR TO THE ANNUAL
CELEBRATION OF THE OSCARS.
>> Reporter: 71-YEAR-OLD GLEN
CLOSE WORE ONE OF THE MOST
TALKED ABOUT GOWNS OF THE
EVENING.
IT WAS EMBROIDERED WITH A
WHOPPING 4 # MILLION BEADS.
>> AND THE DRESS WEIGHS 42
POUNDS.
BUT SHE SAID IT WAS A VERY
SPECIAL NIGHT FOR HER.
TO BE HERE NOMINATED AGAIN AND
SO SHE JUST WANTED TO WEAR
SOMETHING SPECIAL.
>> Reporter: LADY GAGA LOOKED
AMAZING IN HER ALEXANDER
McQUEEN GOWN.
BUT THE REAL BUZZ WAS WHAT SHE
WORE AROUND HER NECK.
A JAW DROPPING 128 KARAT YELLOW
DIAMOND NECKLACE BY TIFFANY.
THE ROCK WAS BOUGHT BY TIFFANY
IN THE YEAR 1878.
THE LAST TIME THE DIAMOND WAS
WORN IN PUBLIC WAS 1962 WHEN
AUDREY HEPBURN WAS PROMOTING
BREAKFAST AT TIFFANY'S.
>> THAT TIFFANY NECKLACE WAS
EVERYTHING.
>> Reporter: LOTS OF BUZZ OVER
KENDALL JENNER'S DRESS.
EXPOSED HER LEGS AND HIPS.
ACTRESS SELMA BLAIR WAS AT THE
PARTY AND HAD TO WALK WITH A
CANE.
IT'S HER FIRST PUBLIC
APPEARANCE SINCE SHE ANNOUNCED
THAT SHE HAS MULTIPLE
SCLEROSIS.
EMMA STONE TURNED HEADS IN A
COPPER AND GOLD DRESS.
THE INTERNET HAD FUN WITH HER
GOWN SAYING IT REMINDED THEM OF
WAFFLES OR MAYBE BACON.
CZAR LEASE HAD PEOPLE TALKING
ABOUT HER DRAMATIC MAKEOVER.
>> SHE WAS UNRECOGNIZABLE.
HER HAIR WAS A DARK BROWN.
SHE HAD THE BOB.
SHE WAS WEARING THIS SKY BLUE
LONG SLEEVE DRESS.
>> Reporter: RACHEL VICE WAS IN
BRIGHT RED BUT HER TWO PIECE
GOWN GOT A THUMBS DOWN.
MAKING THE WORST DRESSED LIST.
>> IT WAS LIKE THIS PLASTIC,
SORT OF RUBBERY CAPE THAT WENT
OVER THE DRESS THAT WOULD HAVE
LOOKED BETTER WITHOUT IT.
>>  Deborah: WE'LL BE BACK WITH
MORE INSIDE EDITION AFTER THIS.
>>> STILL TO COME.
>>  Deborah: DOG VERSES
GODZILLA.
>> THE FAMILY DOG TRAPPED IN A
HOLE BY A TORTOISE NAMED
GODZILLA.
>>> CLOSED CAPTION SPONSORSHIP
FOR INSIDE EDITION IS BROUGHT
TO YOU BY.
>>> STAY TUNED THERE IS MORE
INSIDE EDITION TO COME.
♪ We buy any car dot com ♪
♪ we buy any car dot com ♪
♪ ANY ANY ANY ANY ♪
Did you know trading in your car
at a dealer could cost
you money?
A recent study found consumers
who trade in their car
pay an average of $990
dollars more.
So don't trade in...
sell it....
to We Buy Any Car.
Learn more and get your free
online valuation
now at we buy any car dot com
♪ Find out how much your car is
worth at WeBuyAnyCar.com ♪
>>> FIREFIGHTERS ARE USED TO
DOING ALL KINDS OF RESCUES.
PEOPLE FROM BURNING BUILDINGS,
A CAT OUT OF A TREE, BUT THIS
RESCUE HAD TO BE A FIRST.
>> Reporter: THIS UNLIKELY DUO
JUST GOT THEMSELVES INTO A DEEP
TROUBLE.
A GERMAN SHEPARD NAMED TAYLOR
AND 80-POUND TORTOISE THAT GOES
BY GODZILLA GAVE THEIR OWNERS
QUITE A SCARE WHEN THEY GOT
THEMSELVES JAMMED IN THIS
TUNNEL AND COULDN'T GET OUT.
GODZILLA USES THE TUNNEL TO
HIBERNATE IN THE WINTER BUT
THIS WAS THE FIRST TIME TAYLOR
JOINED HER.
>> I'M THINKING HOW DOES SHE
GET DOWN THERE?
>> Reporter: DAWN TRIED TO SAVE
THE FAMILY PETS HIMSELF BUT
THEN HE GOT STUCK.
>> I WENT HEAD FIRST INTO THE
TOWN WHICH I REALIZE SHORTLY
AFTER WAS A BAD MOVE.
>> Reporter: FINALLY THEY
CALLED THE FIRE DEPARTMENT.
TAYLOR WANTS OUT BUT GODZILLA
IS BLOCKING THE WAY AND WON'T
BUDGE.
THEN THEY OFFER GODZILLA HER
FAVORITE SNACK.
LETTUCE.
GODZILLA GETS OUT OF THE WAY
AND TAYLOR MAKES HER ESCAPE.
>> I WAS VERY RELIEVED.
WE LOVE OUR PETS.
THEY'RE PART OF THE FAMILY AND
WE LOVE THEM.
>>  Deborah: WHEN WE COME BACK
IT'S AN ICE TSUNAMI CAUGHT ON
TAPE.
>>> CLOSED CAPTION SPONSORSHIP
FOR INSIDE EDITION IS BROUGHT
TO YOU BY.
>>> STAY TUNED, THERE IS MORE
INSIDE EDITION TO COME.
>>> THE ICE TSUNAMI.
NEXT.
>>> TRAVEL CONSIDERATION
PROVIDED BY.
>>> FINALLY TODAY WITH ALL THE
WINTER WEATHER HITTING SO MUCH
OF THE COUNTRY, WE HAVE SEEN A
LOT OF EXTREME SITUATIONS
CAUGHT ON TAPE.
BUT HERE'S A NEW ONE.
WE'RE CALLING IT AN ICE
TSUNAMI.
>> Reporter: IT'S THE JAW
DROPPING MOMENT AS HUGE CHUNKS
OF ICE COME BOWLING OVER A
RETAINING WALL.
THE RARE ICE TSUNAMI HAPPENED
NEAR LAKE ERIE AFTER 60 MILES
PER HOUR WINDS PUSHED THE ICE
FROM THE WATER'S SURFACE ON TO
LAND.
THE ICE CHUNKS STACKED UP HIGH
ALL ALONG THE COASTLINE.
>>  Deborah: AND THAT'S INSIDE
EDITION FOR TODAY.
I'M DEBORAH NORVILLE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
Z35WDZ Z16FZ
Y35WDY Y16FY
>> Announcer: TODAY ON AN
ALL-NEW "DR. PHIL."
THEIR DAUGHTER WAS DIAGNOSED
WITH SCHIZOPHRENIA.
MO