Y3671Y YI0Y
>> DICKY: FROM HOLLYWOOD - IT'S
"JIMMY KIMMEL LIVE"!
TONIGHT, REGINA KING.
FROM "THE PUNISHER",
JON BERNTHAL.
THIS WEEK IN UNNECESSARY
CENSORSHIP.
AND MUSIC FROM JUANES.
AND NOW, IN ALL SINCERITY,
JIMMY KIMMEL!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Jimmy: THANK YOU.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WELCOME.
>> Jimmy: THANK YOU.
VERY NICE.
WELCOME.
HI, EVERYBODY, HOW YOU DOING?
VERY NICE.
I'M JIMMY.
HI, EVERYBODY, HOW YOU DOING?
I'M THE HOST OF THE SHOW.
I'M JIMMY.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
I'M THE HOST OF THE SHOW.
WELCOME.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
WELCOME TO HOLLYWOOD.
WELCOME.
APPRECIATE THAT.
WELCOME TO HOLLYWOOD.
HEY, I HAVE A STORY.
APPRECIATE THAT.
SO LAST NIGHT, LAST NIGHT AFTER
HEY, I HAVE A STORY.
THE SHOW, I HOSTED A CONCERT.
SO LAST NIGHT, LAST NIGHT AFTER
IT WAS A BIG CONCERT AT THE
THE SHOW, I HOSTED A CONCERT.
FORUM.
IT WAS A BIG CONCERT AT THE
IT WAS A TRIBUTE TO THE LATE
FORUM.
GREAT CHRIS CORNELL.
IT WAS A TRIBUTE TO THE LATE
WERE YOU THERE?
GREAT CHRIS CORNELL.
IS THAT WHY YOU'RE YELLING?
WERE YOU THERE?
THE LINEUP WAS INCREDIBLE.
IS THAT WHY YOU'RE YELLING?
IT WAS CHRIS STAPLETON.
THE LINEUP WAS INCREDIBLE.
ADAM LEVINE, METALLICA, FOO
IT WAS CHRIS STAPLETON.
FIGHTERS.
ADAM LEVINE, METALLICA, FOO
AMAZING.
FIGHTERS.
YOU HAD FUN, GUILLERMO?
AMAZING.
>> A LOT OF FUN.
YOU HAD FUN, GUILLERMO?
>> Jimmy: GUILLERMO'S LIKE, HEY,
>> A LOT OF FUN.
ARE YOU GOING, LIKE COME WITH --
>> Jimmy: GUILLERMO'S LIKE, HEY,
AT ONE POINT IN THE NIGHT, IT
ARE YOU GOING, LIKE COME WITH --
WAS TWO-THIRDS THROUGH THE SHOW
AT ONE POINT IN THE NIGHT, IT
AND SOMEBODY YELLED WHERE'S
WAS TWO-THIRDS THROUGH THE SHOW
GUILLERMO.
AND SOMEBODY YELLED WHERE'S
SO I GAVE GUILLERMO A SHOUT OUT,
GUILLERMO.
I SAID GUILLERMO'S HERE.
SO I GAVE GUILLERMO A SHOUT OUT,
AND THE WHOLE FORUM ERUPTED IN
I SAID GUILLERMO'S HERE.
CHEERS.
AND THE WHOLE FORUM ERUPTED IN
IT'S LIKE THE SAME REACTION THEY
CHEERS.
GAVE BRAD PITT.
IT'S LIKE THE SAME REACTION THEY
SO I GO BACK STAGE AND TEXT
GAVE BRAD PITT.
GUILLERMO.
SO I GO BACK STAGE AND TEXT
I WANTED TO KNOW WHAT HE
GUILLERMO.
THOUGHT.
I WANTED TO KNOW WHAT HE
AND WHERE WERE YOU WHEN YOU GOT
THOUGHT.
THE TEXT I SENT YOU?
AND WHERE WERE YOU WHEN YOU GOT
>> I WAS AT HOME.
THE TEXT I SENT YOU?
>> Jimmy: HE WAS AT HOME.
>> I WAS AT HOME.
AFTER METALLICA, HE DITCHED US,
>> Jimmy: HE WAS AT HOME.
GOT IN A UBER AND WENT HOME.
AFTER METALLICA, HE DITCHED US,
IN ALL FAIRNESS, HE HAS TO GO TO
GOT IN A UBER AND WENT HOME.
BED EARLY, BECAUSE HE'S GOT TO
IN ALL FAIRNESS, HE HAS TO GO TO
BE AT WORK AT 2:00 P.M.
BED EARLY, BECAUSE HE'S GOT TO
TODAY IS DAY 27 OF THE
BE AT WORK AT 2:00 P.M.
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
TODAY IS DAY 27 OF THE
REMEMBER WHEN TRUMP SAID HE'D
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
RUN THE COUNTRY LIKE A BUSINESS?
REMEMBER WHEN TRUMP SAID HE'D
TURNS OUT THE BUSINESS IS RADIO
RUN THE COUNTRY LIKE A BUSINESS?
SHACK.
TURNS OUT THE BUSINESS IS RADIO
[ APPLAUSE ]
SHACK.
HE IS DESPERATELY TRYING TO PIN
[ APPLAUSE ]
BLAME ON THE SHUTDOWN ON THE
HE IS DESPERATELY TRYING TO PIN
DEMOCRATS.
BLAME ON THE SHUTDOWN ON THE
HE WROTE TOTALLY UNHINGED.
DEMOCRATS.
THEY NO LONGER CARE FOR MA IS
HE WROTE TOTALLY UNHINGED.
RIGHT FOR THE COUNTRY.
THEY NO LONGER CARE FOR MA IS
HE'S JUST AS GOOD AT SPELLING
RIGHT FOR THE COUNTRY.
COUNTRY AS HE IS RUNNING IN IT.
HE'S JUST AS GOOD AT SPELLING
MOST OF HIS IRE IS DIRECTED AT
COUNTRY AS HE IS RUNNING IN IT.
NANCY PELOSI, THE SPEAKER OF THE
MOST OF HIS IRE IS DIRECTED AT
HOUSE.
NANCY PELOSI, THE SPEAKER OF THE
YESTERDAY SHE SENT HIM A LETTER,
HOUSE.
SUGGESTING HE POSTPONE THE STATE
YESTERDAY SHE SENT HIM A LETTER,
OF THE UNION ADDRESS UNTIL THE
SUGGESTING HE POSTPONE THE STATE
SHUTDOWN IS OVER.
OF THE UNION ADDRESS UNTIL THE
SHE WILL NOT PERMIT HIM TO GIVE
SHUTDOWN IS OVER.
IT FROM THE HOUSE OF
SHE WILL NOT PERMIT HIM TO GIVE
REPRESENTATIVES.
IT FROM THE HOUSE OF
SO TODAY, TRUMP RETALIATED IN A
REPRESENTATIVES.
LETTER OF HIS OWN, TELLING HER
SO TODAY, TRUMP RETALIATED IN A
THAT HE WAS CANCELING HER FLIGHT
LETTER OF HIS OWN, TELLING HER
TO AFGHANISTAN.
THAT HE WAS CANCELING HER FLIGHT
SHE WAS GOING ON MILITARY
TO AFGHANISTAN.
AIRCRAFT.
SHE WAS GOING ON MILITARY
AND HE SAID IF SHE WANTED TO GO,
AIRCRAFT.
SHE COULD FLY COMMERCIAL, TO A
AND HE SAID IF SHE WANTED TO GO,
WAR ZONE.
SHE COULD FLY COMMERCIAL, TO A
AND HE SENT THE LETTER LESS THAN
WAR ZONE.
AN HOUR BEFORE SHE WAS SUPPOSED
AND HE SENT THE LETTER LESS THAN
TO LEAVE.
AN HOUR BEFORE SHE WAS SUPPOSED
IT WAS THE EQUIVALENT OF YOU
TO LEAVE.
BREAK UP WITH ME?
IT WAS THE EQUIVALENT OF YOU
I BREAK UP WITH YOU.
BREAK UP WITH ME?
I BET HE WAS SO DELIGHTED WITH
I BREAK UP WITH YOU.
HIMSELF WHEN HE CAME UP WITH THE
I BET HE WAS SO DELIGHTED WITH
IDEA.
HIMSELF WHEN HE CAME UP WITH THE
AN OFFICIAL FROM THE WHITE HOUSE
IDEA.
SAID HE SPENT THE DAY WATCHING
AN OFFICIAL FROM THE WHITE HOUSE
COVERAGE OF IT AND WAS VERY
SAID HE SPENT THE DAY WATCHING
PLEASED THIS AFTERNOON.
COVERAGE OF IT AND WAS VERY
HE MAY BE THE ONLY ONE PLEASED
PLEASED THIS AFTERNOON.
BECAUSE EVEN SOME OF HIS FELLOW
HE MAY BE THE ONLY ONE PLEASED
REPUBLICANS SAID THIS WAS A
BECAUSE EVEN SOME OF HIS FELLOW
PETTY THING TO DO.
REPUBLICANS SAID THIS WAS A
AND ALL THE DEMOCRATS ARE MAD.
PETTY THING TO DO.
THIS IS FROM CNN TODAY.
AND ALL THE DEMOCRATS ARE MAD.
PHIL MATTINGLY STOPPED STENY
THIS IS FROM CNN TODAY.
HOYER LIKE THIS.
PHIL MATTINGLY STOPPED STENY
>> HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
HOYER LIKE THIS.
HERE'S HOUSE MAJORITY LEADER
>> HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
STENY HOYER TALKING ABOUT WHAT'S
HERE'S HOUSE MAJORITY LEADER
GOING ON.
STENY HOYER TALKING ABOUT WHAT'S
>> Jimmy: HOLD ON A SECOND.
GOING ON.
THAT IS THE MOST THREATENING
>> Jimmy: HOLD ON A SECOND.
MICROPHONE I'VE EVER SEEN IN MY
THAT IS THE MOST THREATENING
LIFE.
MICROPHONE I'VE EVER SEEN IN MY
[ APPLAUSE ]
LIFE.
GIVE ME YOUR MONEY, OLD MAN!
[ APPLAUSE ]
DESPERATE TIMES, I GUESS.
GIVE ME YOUR MONEY, OLD MAN!
YOU KNOW, IF THE DEMOCRATS CAN'T
DESPERATE TIMES, I GUESS.
CONVINCE TRUMP TO END THIS SILLY
YOU KNOW, IF THE DEMOCRATS CAN'T
SHUTDOWN, I THINK I KNOW
CONVINCE TRUMP TO END THIS SILLY
SOMEBODY WHO CAN.
SHUTDOWN, I THINK I KNOW
A LOT OF PEOPLE TRY TO MAKE
SOMEBODY WHO CAN.
SENSE OUT OF THIS.
A LOT OF PEOPLE TRY TO MAKE
THE CLEAREST VOICE I'VE HEARD ON
SENSE OUT OF THIS.
THE SUBJECT SO FAR, BELIEVE IT
THE CLEAREST VOICE I'VE HEARD ON
OR NOT, CAME FROM CARDI B.
THE SUBJECT SO FAR, BELIEVE IT
>> HEY, Y'ALL, I JUST WANT TO
OR NOT, CAME FROM CARDI B.
REMIND Y'ALL.
>> HEY, Y'ALL, I JUST WANT TO
IT'S BEEN A LITTLE OVER THREE
REMIND Y'ALL.
WEEKS.
IT'S BEEN A LITTLE OVER THREE
IT'S BEEN A LITTLE BIT OVER
WEEKS.
THREE WEEKS.
IT'S BEEN A LITTLE BIT OVER
TRUMP IS NOW ORDERING FEDERAL
THREE WEEKS.
GOVERNMENT WORKERS TO GO BACK TO
TRUMP IS NOW ORDERING FEDERAL
WORK WITHOUT GETTING PAID.
GOVERNMENT WORKERS TO GO BACK TO
NOW I DON'T WANT TO HERE YOUR
WORK WITHOUT GETTING PAID.
[BLEEP] TALKING ABOUT OH, BUT
NOW I DON'T WANT TO HERE YOUR
OBAMA SHUT DOWN THE GOVERNMENT
[BLEEP] TALKING ABOUT OH, BUT
FOR 17 DAYS, YEAH, BITCH, BUT
OBAMA SHUT DOWN THE GOVERNMENT
HEALTH CARE, SO YOUR GRANDMA CAN
FOR 17 DAYS, YEAH, BITCH, BUT
CHECK HER BLOOD PRESSURE, AND
HEALTH CARE, SO YOUR GRANDMA CAN
YOU WHAT TO [ BLEEP ],
CHECK HER BLOOD PRESSURE, AND
[ BLEEP ].
YOU WHAT TO [ BLEEP ],
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ BLEEP ].
>> Jimmy: CARDI B IS RIGHT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
ALMOST 800,000 FEDERAL EMPLOYEES
>> Jimmy: CARDI B IS RIGHT.
ARE NOT GETTING PAID.
ALMOST 800,000 FEDERAL EMPLOYEES
AND EVERY NIGHT UNTIL THIS IS
ARE NOT GETTING PAID.
OVER, WE'RE HIRING A FURLOUGHED
AND EVERY NIGHT UNTIL THIS IS
WORKER PER NIGHT.
OVER, WE'RE HIRING A FURLOUGHED
LAST NIGHT WE BROUGHT IN A NASA
WORKER PER NIGHT.
ENGINEER WHO'S OUT OF WORK.
LAST NIGHT WE BROUGHT IN A NASA
LET'S SAY HELLO TO OUR NEW
ENGINEER WHO'S OUT OF WORK.
EMPLOYEE TONIGHT.
LET'S SAY HELLO TO OUR NEW
LET'S WELCOME ANDREW RAGOPPOLIS.
EMPLOYEE TONIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
LET'S WELCOME ANDREW RAGOPPOLIS.
TELL US WHAT YOU DO
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
SPECIFICALLY.
TELL US WHAT YOU DO
>> I'M A STATION RANGER AT
SPECIFICALLY.
CABRILLO NATIONAL MONUMENT.
>> I'M A STATION RANGER AT
>> Jimmy: WE STILL HAVE NATIONAL
CABRILLO NATIONAL MONUMENT.
PARKS, CORRECT?
>> Jimmy: WE STILL HAVE NATIONAL
>> WE DO.
PARKS, CORRECT?
>> Jimmy: THAT'S A GOOD SIGN,
>> WE DO.
RIGHT?
>> Jimmy: THAT'S A GOOD SIGN,
>> WELL, IF PEOPLE VISIT AND
RIGHT?
DAMAGE THEM, WE WON'T HAVE THEM
>> WELL, IF PEOPLE VISIT AND
ANYMORE.
DAMAGE THEM, WE WON'T HAVE THEM
>> Jimmy: RIGHT NOW THERE'S
ANYMORE.
NOBODY WORKING AT THE PARK YOU
>> Jimmy: RIGHT NOW THERE'S
WORK AT.
NOBODY WORKING AT THE PARK YOU
>> NO, WE HAVE A CREW OF RANGERS
WORK AT.
WHO WATCH IT TO MAKE SURE OUR
>> NO, WE HAVE A CREW OF RANGERS
RESOURCES AREN'T DAMAGED.
WHO WATCH IT TO MAKE SURE OUR
>> Jimmy: YOU ARE A
RESOURCES AREN'T DAMAGED.
NON-ESSENTIAL GOVERNMENT
>> Jimmy: YOU ARE A
EMPLOYEE?
NON-ESSENTIAL GOVERNMENT
>> YEAH, I STAY HOME AND WATCH A
EMPLOYEE?
LOT OF NETFLIX.
>> YEAH, I STAY HOME AND WATCH A
>> Jimmy: YOU CAME UP WITH AN
LOT OF NETFLIX.
IDEA FOR A JOB THAT I LIKE.
>> Jimmy: YOU CAME UP WITH AN
>> I PITCHED IT TO MY BROTHER
IDEA FOR A JOB THAT I LIKE.
FIRST.
>> I PITCHED IT TO MY BROTHER
>> Jimmy: WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
FIRST.
DO FOR US TONIGHT?
>> Jimmy: WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
>> I'M GOING TO TAKE CARE OF OUR
DO FOR US TONIGHT?
URBAN LANDSCAPE AND WATER YOUR
>> I'M GOING TO TAKE CARE OF OUR
PLANTS.
URBAN LANDSCAPE AND WATER YOUR
>> Jimmy: NOW WE DON'T HAVE MANY
PLANTS.
PLANTS, BUT IF YOU SEE ANY,
>> Jimmy: NOW WE DON'T HAVE MANY
WATER THEM.
PLANTS, BUT IF YOU SEE ANY,
>> OKAY.
WATER THEM.
>> Jimmy: THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> OKAY.
APPRECIATE IT.
>> Jimmy: THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
APPRECIATE IT.
OH, ANDREW.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I FORGOT, WE HAVE TO GIVE YOU
OH, ANDREW.
THIS.
I FORGOT, WE HAVE TO GIVE YOU
IN CASE YOU DON'T HAVE ONE OF
THIS.
YOUR OWN.
IN CASE YOU DON'T HAVE ONE OF
IF YOU SEE ANY FUNNY-LOOKING
YOUR OWN.
PLANTS, JUST IGNORE THEM, OKAY?
IF YOU SEE ANY FUNNY-LOOKING
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
PLANTS, JUST IGNORE THEM, OKAY?
THAT'S ANDREW, ANDREW IS OUR --
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THAT'S ANDREW, ANDREW IS OUR --
THE PRESIDENT APPEARS TO BE ON A
[ APPLAUSE ]
COLLUSION CASE WITH THE LAW
THE PRESIDENT APPEARS TO BE ON A
RIGHT NOW, HIS ALLEGED LAWYER,
COLLUSION CASE WITH THE LAW
RUDY GIULIANI WAS ON AIR LAST
RIGHT NOW, HIS ALLEGED LAWYER,
NIGHT.
RUDY GIULIANI WAS ON AIR LAST
AND RUDIER THAN EVER.
NIGHT.
HE MADE A CRAZY APPEARANCE ON
AND RUDIER THAN EVER.
CHRIS CUOMO'S SHOW.
HE MADE A CRAZY APPEARANCE ON
IF WE DIDN'T HAVE IT ON VIDEO IT
CHRIS CUOMO'S SHOW.
WOULD BE ALMOST TOO MUCH TO
IF WE DIDN'T HAVE IT ON VIDEO IT
BELIEVE.
WOULD BE ALMOST TOO MUCH TO
>> THE AMOUNT OF FALSE REPORTING
BELIEVE.
ABOUT THIS CASE IS DESPICABLE.
>> THE AMOUNT OF FALSE REPORTING
>> FALSE REPORTING IS SAYING
ABOUT THIS CASE IS DESPICABLE.
NOBODY IN THE CAMPAIGN HAD ANY
>> FALSE REPORTING IS SAYING
CONTACT WITH RUSSIA.
NOBODY IN THE CAMPAIGN HAD ANY
FALSE REPORTING IS SAYING
CONTACT WITH RUSSIA.
THERE'S NO SUGGESTION OF ANY
FALSE REPORTING IS SAYING
KIND OF COLLUSION BETWEEN THE
THERE'S NO SUGGESTION OF ANY
CAMPAIGN AND ANY RUSSIANS
KIND OF COLLUSION BETWEEN THE
BECAUSE NOW YOU HAVE PAUL
CAMPAIGN AND ANY RUSSIANS
MANAFORT GIVING POLL DATA.
BECAUSE NOW YOU HAVE PAUL
>> YOU JUST MISSTATED MY
MANAFORT GIVING POLL DATA.
POSITION.
>> YOU JUST MISSTATED MY
I NEVER SAID THERE WAS NO
POSITION.
COLLUSION BETWEEN THE CAMPAIGN
I NEVER SAID THERE WAS NO
OR BETWEEN PEOPLE IN THE
COLLUSION BETWEEN THE CAMPAIGN
CAMPAIGN.
OR BETWEEN PEOPLE IN THE
>> YES, YOU HAVE.
CAMPAIGN.
>> NO, I HAVE NOT.
>> YES, YOU HAVE.
I SAID THE PRESIDENT OF THE
>> NO, I HAVE NOT.
UNITED STATES.
I SAID THE PRESIDENT OF THE
THERE HAS BEEN NO EVIDENCE THAT
UNITED STATES.
THE PRESIDENT HAS COMMITTED THE
THERE HAS BEEN NO EVIDENCE THAT
ONLY CRIME THAT COULD BE
THE PRESIDENT HAS COMMITTED THE
COMMITTED HERE, CONSPIRING WITH
ONLY CRIME THAT COULD BE
THE RUSSIANS TO HACK THE DNC.
COMMITTED HERE, CONSPIRING WITH
>> Jimmy: NOBODY IN THE TRUMP
THE RUSSIANS TO HACK THE DNC.
ADMINISTRATION EVER SAID ANY OF
>> Jimmy: NOBODY IN THE TRUMP
THE THINGS THEY SAY ALL THE
ADMINISTRATION EVER SAID ANY OF
TIME.
THE THINGS THEY SAY ALL THE
BUT THERE MUST BE ANOTHER RUDY
TIME.
GIULIANI OUT THERE WHO'S BEEN
BUT THERE MUST BE ANOTHER RUDY
GOING AROUND SAYING THERE WAS NO
GIULIANI OUT THERE WHO'S BEEN
COLLUSION BETWEEN RUSSIA AND THE
GOING AROUND SAYING THERE WAS NO
CAMPAIGN.
COLLUSION BETWEEN RUSSIA AND THE
>> IS IT STILL THE POSITION OF
CAMPAIGN.
YOU AND YOUR CLIENT THAT THERE
>> IS IT STILL THE POSITION OF
WAS NO COLLUSION WITH THE
YOU AND YOUR CLIENT THAT THERE
RUSSIANS, WHATSOEVER, ON BEHALF
WAS NO COLLUSION WITH THE
OF THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN?
RUSSIANS, WHATSOEVER, ON BEHALF
>> CORRECT.
OF THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN?
>> Jimmy: CORRECT.
>> CORRECT.
SO HE DID SAY IT.
>> Jimmy: CORRECT.
THE SUREST SIGN OF HOW SCREWED
SO HE DID SAY IT.
UP THIS ADMINISTRATION IS, IS
THE SUREST SIGN OF HOW SCREWED
THAT RUDY GIULIANI IS STILL
UP THIS ADMINISTRATION IS, IS
ALLOWED TO GO ON TV TO SPEAK ON
THAT RUDY GIULIANI IS STILL
THEIR BEHALF.
ALLOWED TO GO ON TV TO SPEAK ON
GO ON, RUDY.
THEIR BEHALF.
>> THE PRESIDENT DID NOT.
GO ON, RUDY.
>> YOU SAID HE HAD NO CONTACT.
>> THE PRESIDENT DID NOT.
THE GUY RUNNING HIS CAMPAIGN WAS
>> YOU SAID HE HAD NO CONTACT.
WORKING ON AN ISSUE AT THE SAME
THE GUY RUNNING HIS CAMPAIGN WAS
TIME AS THE CONVENTION.
WORKING ON AN ISSUE AT THE SAME
>> HE SAID HE DIDN'T.
TIME AS THE CONVENTION.
HE DIDN'T SAY NOBODY.
>> HE SAID HE DIDN'T.
HOW WOULD YOU KNOW THAT NOBODY
HE DIDN'T SAY NOBODY.
IN YOUR CAMPAIGN.
HOW WOULD YOU KNOW THAT NOBODY
>> HE ACTUALLY DID SAY THAT,
IN YOUR CAMPAIGN.
RUDY.
>> HE ACTUALLY DID SAY THAT,
THEN HE SAID NOBODY THAT HE
RUDY.
KNEW.
THEN HE SAID NOBODY THAT HE
>> Jimmy: THE TRUTH IS, IT
KNEW.
DOESN'T MATTER WHAT RUDY
>> Jimmy: THE TRUTH IS, IT
GIULIANI SAYS, HE'S NOT THE ONE
DOESN'T MATTER WHAT RUDY
BEING INVESTIGATED YET.
GIULIANI SAYS, HE'S NOT THE ONE
WHAT MATTERS IS, DID THE
BEING INVESTIGATED YET.
PRESIDENT SAY THERE WAS NO
WHAT MATTERS IS, DID THE
COLLUSION BETWEEN THE RUSSIANS
PRESIDENT SAY THERE WAS NO
AND HIS CAMPAIGN.
COLLUSION BETWEEN THE RUSSIANS
>> THERE WAS NO COLLUSION
AND HIS CAMPAIGN.
BETWEEN THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND
>> THERE WAS NO COLLUSION
THE RUSSIAN PEOPLE.
BETWEEN THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND
>> Jimmy: YEAH.
THE RUSSIAN PEOPLE.
AT SOME POINT, RUDY IS GOING TO
>> Jimmy: YEAH.
HAVE TO DENY THAT TRUMP IS EVEN
AT SOME POINT, RUDY IS GOING TO
THE PRESIDENT.
HAVE TO DENY THAT TRUMP IS EVEN
BUT THE IMPORTANT THING IN
THE PRESIDENT.
GIULIANI'S MIND IS THAT ROBERT
BUT THE IMPORTANT THING IN
MUELLER PUT THIS THING TO REST.
GIULIANI'S MIND IS THAT ROBERT
>> HE PUTS OUT THE REPORT AND
MUELLER PUT THIS THING TO REST.
THEN WE GET AND SEE WHAT IT
>> HE PUTS OUT THE REPORT AND
SAYS.
THEN WE GET AND SEE WHAT IT
I'VE ALWAYS SEEN THIS AS A FALSE
SAYS.
ARGUMENT OF HE'S NOT SHOWING US
I'VE ALWAYS SEEN THIS AS A FALSE
WHAT HE HAS.
ARGUMENT OF HE'S NOT SHOWING US
IT'S NOT OVER.
WHAT HE HAS.
>> LET'S DO IT.
IT'S NOT OVER.
>> HE HAS TO FINISH.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> WHAT DID YOU MEAN?
>> HE HAS TO FINISH.
>> HOW MUCH LONGER?
>> WHAT DID YOU MEAN?
>> HE JUST PUT OUT THAT HIS
>> HOW MUCH LONGER?
CAMPAIGN CHAIRMAN WAS PLAYING
>> HE JUST PUT OUT THAT HIS
WITH THE RUSSIANS.
CAMPAIGN CHAIRMAN WAS PLAYING
>> WE DON'T NEED A SPECIAL
WITH THE RUSSIANS.
COUNSEL TO INVESTIGATE A
>> WE DON'T NEED A SPECIAL
CAMPAIGN CHAIR.
COUNSEL TO INVESTIGATE A
>> Jimmy: POOR RUDY.
CAMPAIGN CHAIR.
SOMEDAY HE'S GOING TO BE IN A
>> Jimmy: POOR RUDY.
MENTAL FACILITY TELLING PEOPLE
SOMEDAY HE'S GOING TO BE IN A
THAT HE USED TO BE THE MAYOR OF
MENTAL FACILITY TELLING PEOPLE
NEW YORK AND PEOPLE WILL BE
THAT HE USED TO BE THE MAYOR OF
LIKE, UH-HUH.
NEW YORK AND PEOPLE WILL BE
[ APPLAUSE ]
LIKE, UH-HUH.
SO IN THE MEANTIME WHILE THAT'S
[ APPLAUSE ]
GOING ON THERE, WE HAVE NEW
SO IN THE MEANTIME WHILE THAT'S
INFORMATION ABOUT THE
GOING ON THERE, WE HAVE NEW
PRESIDENT'S FORMER LAWYER,
INFORMATION ABOUT THE
MICHAEL COHEN.
PRESIDENT'S FORMER LAWYER,
ACCORDING TO THE WALL STREET
MICHAEL COHEN.
JOURNAL,
ACCORDING TO THE WALL STREET
IN THE LEADUP TO THE RUN FOR
JOURNAL,
PRESIDENT, HE HIRED AN ONLINE
IN THE LEADUP TO THE RUN FOR
COMPANY TO RIG POLLS IN HIS
PRESIDENT, HE HIRED AN ONLINE
FAVOR.
COMPANY TO RIG POLLS IN HIS
COHEN SAYS THE PRESIDENT
FAVOR.
DIRECTED HIM TO USE TWO POLLS.
COHEN SAYS THE PRESIDENT
EVEN THOSE DIDN'T WORK OUT.
DIRECTED HIM TO USE TWO POLLS.
NOT ONLY DID HE NOT WIN EITHER
EVEN THOSE DIDN'T WORK OUT.
OF THE POLLS, I THINK HE DIDN'T
NOT ONLY DID HE NOT WIN EITHER
EVEN CRACK THE TOP 100.
OF THE POLLS, I THINK HE DIDN'T
THE GUY COHEN HIRED TO DO THIS,
EVEN CRACK THE TOP 100.
SHOWED UP AT TRUMP TOWER LOOKING
THE GUY COHEN HIRED TO DO THIS,
FOR $50,000 HE WAS OWED.
SHOWED UP AT TRUMP TOWER LOOKING
AND WHEN HE DID, COHEN GAVE HIM
FOR $50,000 HE WAS OWED.
A WALMART BAG WITH $12,000 TO
AND WHEN HE DID, COHEN GAVE HIM
$13,000 IN CASH AND A BOXING
A WALMART BAG WITH $12,000 TO
GLOVE HE CLAIMED HAD BEEN
$13,000 IN CASH AND A BOXING
WORN BY A BRAZILIAN MMA FIGHTER.
GLOVE HE CLAIMED HAD BEEN
IT'S LIKE A SCENE OUT OF THE
WORN BY A BRAZILIAN MMA FIGHTER.
WORST HEIST MOVIE, OCEANS
IT'S LIKE A SCENE OUT OF THE
CHAPTER 11.
WORST HEIST MOVIE, OCEANS
THE GOON COHEN HIRED HAS A I.T.
CHAPTER 11.
COMPANY.
THE GOON COHEN HIRED HAS A I.T.
HIS NAME IS JOHN GOGGARD.
COMPANY.
THIS TAPE HE MADE TRYING TO GET
HIS NAME IS JOHN GOGGARD.
ON SURVIVOR IN 2005 TELLS YOU
THIS TAPE HE MADE TRYING TO GET
ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW.
ON SURVIVOR IN 2005 TELLS YOU
>> IN MY LINE OF BUSINESS, I
ALL YOU NEED TO KNOW.
DEAL WITH PEOPLE AROUND THE
>> IN MY LINE OF BUSINESS, I
GLOBE ON A DAILY BASIS.
DEAL WITH PEOPLE AROUND THE
THIS HAS GIVEN ME THE UNCANNY
GLOBE ON A DAILY BASIS.
ABILITY TO MAKE ANYBODY LOVE ME.
THIS HAS GIVEN ME THE UNCANNY
THIS WILL MAKE ME BE THE
ABILITY TO MAKE ANYBODY LOVE ME.
MOST-LOVED SURVIVOR CONTESTANT
THIS WILL MAKE ME BE THE
OF ALL TIMES.
MOST-LOVED SURVIVOR CONTESTANT
AND MAYBE THE MOST HATED, TOO.
OF ALL TIMES.
>> Jimmy: ONLY THE BEST PEOPLE,
AND MAYBE THE MOST HATED, TOO.
YOU KNOW?
>> Jimmy: ONLY THE BEST PEOPLE,
LITERALLY EVERYONE AROUND TRUMP
YOU KNOW?
IS A CHARACTER FROM A REALITY
LITERALLY EVERYONE AROUND TRUMP
SHOW.
IS A CHARACTER FROM A REALITY
AND THAT IS NOT EVEN THE BEST
SHOW.
PART OF THE STORY.
AND THAT IS NOT EVEN THE BEST
SO COHEN ALSO ASKED THE GUY,
PART OF THE STORY.
WHILE HE'S DOING THIS, TO SET UP
SO COHEN ALSO ASKED THE GUY,
A TWITTER ACCOUNT CALLED WOMEN
WHILE HE'S DOING THIS, TO SET UP
FOR COHEN.
A TWITTER ACCOUNT CALLED WOMEN
THIS IS A REAL ACCOUNT, CREATED
FOR COHEN.
BACK IN 2016.
THIS IS A REAL ACCOUNT, CREATED
IT'S FOR QUOTE, WOMEN WHO LOVE
BACK IN 2016.
AND SUPPORT MICHAEL COHEN.
IT'S FOR QUOTE, WOMEN WHO LOVE
STRONG, PITTS BULL, SEX SYMBOL,
AND SUPPORT MICHAEL COHEN.
NO NONSENSE.
STRONG, PITTS BULL, SEX SYMBOL,
BASICALLY, COHEN ASKED THIS GUY,
NO NONSENSE.
HELP ME RIG THE ELECTION, WHILE
BASICALLY, COHEN ASKED THIS GUY,
YOU'RE AT IT, COULD YOU MAKE
HELP ME RIG THE ELECTION, WHILE
PEOPLE THINK GIRLS LIKE ME, TOO?
YOU'RE AT IT, COULD YOU MAKE
BECAUSE I LOVED THIS, I CLICKED
PEOPLE THINK GIRLS LIKE ME, TOO?
TO SEE WHO WAS FOLLOWING THIS
BECAUSE I LOVED THIS, I CLICKED
ACCOUNT, AND SOME OF THE WOMEN
TO SEE WHO WAS FOLLOWING THIS
FOLLOWING HIM ARE NAMED ELVIS,
ACCOUNT, AND SOME OF THE WOMEN
JOHN, TED, SONNY, WE ALSO HAVE
FOLLOWING HIM ARE NAMED ELVIS,
STEVE, AND BILL.
JOHN, TED, SONNY, WE ALSO HAVE
AND THESE ARE SOME OF THE THINGS
STEVE, AND BILL.
THEY TWEETED.
AND THESE ARE SOME OF THE THINGS
SNAZZY LOOKING AND READY TO
THEY TWEETED.
MAGA.
SNAZZY LOOKING AND READY TO
BEST LOOKING LOVE AWARD GOES TO,
MAGA.
HEART EMOJI.
BEST LOOKING LOVE AWARD GOES TO,
WE LOVE YOU GUYS.
HEART EMOJI.
THIS HAS GOT TO BE THE SADDEST
WE LOVE YOU GUYS.
THING I'VE EVER HEARD OF IN MY
THIS HAS GOT TO BE THE SADDEST
LIFE.
THING I'VE EVER HEARD OF IN MY
WE'RE A WEEK AWAY FROM HEARING
LIFE.
TO SEND DIRTY TEXTS TO HIMSELF.
WE'RE A WEEK AWAY FROM HEARING
HE MIGHT BE A LOT MORE HILARIOUS
TO SEND DIRTY TEXTS TO HIMSELF.
THAN I EVER IMAGINED.
HE MIGHT BE A LOT MORE HILARIOUS
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HEARD ABOUT
THAN I EVER IMAGINED.
THIS.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HEARD ABOUT
BUT YOUTUBE, ARE YOU FAMILIAR
THIS.
WITH YOUTUBE?
BUT YOUTUBE, ARE YOU FAMILIAR
YOUTUBE IS CRACKING DOWN.
WITH YOUTUBE?
THEY ANNOUNCED THAT THEY'RE
YOUTUBE IS CRACKING DOWN.
BANNING DANGEROUS PRANKS AND
THEY ANNOUNCED THAT THEY'RE
CHALLENGES FROM THEIR PLATFORM.
BANNING DANGEROUS PRANKS AND
THEY POSTED THIS, DANGEROUS
CHALLENGES FROM THEIR PLATFORM.
PRANKS AND CHALLENGES POST
THEY POSTED THIS, DANGEROUS
UPDATE.
PRANKS AND CHALLENGES POST
HI, EVERYBODY.
UPDATE.
YOUTUBE IS HOME TO MANY VIRAL
HI, EVERYBODY.
CHALLENGES AND PRANKS LIKE JIMMY
YOUTUBE IS HOME TO MANY VIRAL
KIMMEL'S TERRIBLE CHRISTMAS
CHALLENGES AND PRANKS LIKE JIMMY
PRESENTS PRANK.
KIMMEL'S TERRIBLE CHRISTMAS
THANK YOU.
PRESENTS PRANK.
OR THE WATER BOTTLE FLIP
THANK YOU.
CHALLENGE.
OR THE WATER BOTTLE FLIP
WE ALWAYS HAVE POLICIES TO MAKE
CHALLENGE.
SURE WHAT'S FUNNY DOESN'T CROSS
WE ALWAYS HAVE POLICIES TO MAKE
THE LINE, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
SURE WHAT'S FUNNY DOESN'T CROSS
>> BASICALLY YOUTUBE HAS JUST
THE LINE, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
BANNED YOUTUBE VIDEOS.
>> BASICALLY YOUTUBE HAS JUST
SOMEBODY WHO LIKES A GOOD PRANK
BANNED YOUTUBE VIDEOS.
AND LIKES TO DO THEM, IT'S SAD
SOMEBODY WHO LIKES A GOOD PRANK
THAT A FEW BAD APPLES HAD TO
AND LIKES TO DO THEM, IT'S SAD
RUIN EATING POISONOUS DETERGENT
THAT A FEW BAD APPLES HAD TO
PACKETS FOR EVERYONE.
RUIN EATING POISONOUS DETERGENT
THE BIGGER QUESTION IS HOW DO
PACKETS FOR EVERYONE.
YOU KNOW, BEFORE YOU DO
THE BIGGER QUESTION IS HOW DO
SOMETHING, WHAT'S DANGEROUS AND
YOU KNOW, BEFORE YOU DO
WHAT'S NOT?
SOMETHING, WHAT'S DANGEROUS AND
WE'VE DONE SOME THINGS THAT
WHAT'S NOT?
COULD GO IN A DANGEROUS
WE'VE DONE SOME THINGS THAT
SITUATION.
COULD GO IN A DANGEROUS
SO I WENT OVER THERE AND
SITUATION.
RAN SOME IDEAS BY THEIR CONTENT
SO I WENT OVER THERE AND
EXECUTIVE.
RAN SOME IDEAS BY THEIR CONTENT
HI THERE, HOW ARE YOU?
EXECUTIVE.
THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
HI THERE, HOW ARE YOU?
>> OF COURSE.
THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> Jimmy: SO I WAS READING ABOUT
>> OF COURSE.
THESE NEW RULES THAT YOU HAVE
>> Jimmy: SO I WAS READING ABOUT
WITH THE YOUTUBE CHALLENGES, AND
THESE NEW RULES THAT YOU HAVE
I'M A LITTLE BIT CONCERNED ABOUT
WITH THE YOUTUBE CHALLENGES, AND
IT BECAUSE WE DO A LOT OF THAT
I'M A LITTLE BIT CONCERNED ABOUT
KIND OF STUFF ON THE SHOW.
IT BECAUSE WE DO A LOT OF THAT
>> WELL, I MEAN WE TRUST WHAT
KIND OF STUFF ON THE SHOW.
YOU DO, THAT'S A DIFFERENT
>> WELL, I MEAN WE TRUST WHAT
SITUATION.
YOU DO, THAT'S A DIFFERENT
>> Jimmy: SO I CAN DO ANYTHING?
SITUATION.
>> WELL, NOT ANYTHING.
>> Jimmy: SO I CAN DO ANYTHING?
>> Jimmy: LET ME RUN SOME THINGS
>> WELL, NOT ANYTHING.
BY YOU, THERE'S THINGS WE'RE
>> Jimmy: LET ME RUN SOME THINGS
WORKING ON.
BY YOU, THERE'S THINGS WE'RE
>> SURE.
WORKING ON.
>> Jimmy: THE, I BET YOU CAN'T
>> SURE.
EAT ALL THE KNIVES CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: THE, I BET YOU CAN'T
>> WELL, NO, I WOULD SAY NOT
EAT ALL THE KNIVES CHALLENGE.
THAT ONE.
>> WELL, NO, I WOULD SAY NOT
>> Jimmy: THAT'S A NO?
THAT ONE.
THE SETTING MY BROTHER ON FIRE
>> Jimmy: THAT'S A NO?
CHALLENGE.
THE SETTING MY BROTHER ON FIRE
>> THAT SOUNDS DANGEROUS, NO.
CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: DAD, I BOILED THE
>> THAT SOUNDS DANGEROUS, NO.
TOASTER CHALLENGE WHILE IT'S
>> Jimmy: DAD, I BOILED THE
PLUGGED IN.
TOASTER CHALLENGE WHILE IT'S
>> NO.
PLUGGED IN.
>> Jimmy: THE GHOST PEPPER UP
>> NO.
THE BUTT CHALLENGE?
>> Jimmy: THE GHOST PEPPER UP
>> NO.
THE BUTT CHALLENGE?
>> Jimmy: THE BLIND FOLDED BOW
>> NO.
CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: THE BLIND FOLDED BOW
>> NO.
CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: THE JUMP THE ZOOM
>> NO.
FENCE CHALLENGE?
>> Jimmy: THE JUMP THE ZOOM
>> NO.
FENCE CHALLENGE?
>> Jimmy: ASBESTOS TO BABY
>> NO.
POWDER CHALLENGE?
>> Jimmy: ASBESTOS TO BABY
>> NO.
POWDER CHALLENGE?
>> Jimmy: LET'S MAKES FRIENDS ON
>> NO.
CRAIGSLIST CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: LET'S MAKES FRIENDS ON
>> WELL, I MEAN WE WOULD NEED
CRAIGSLIST CHALLENGE.
TO --
>> WELL, I MEAN WE WOULD NEED
>> Jimmy: SEAT BELTS ARE FOR
TO --
SNOWFLAKES CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: SEAT BELTS ARE FOR
>> NO.
SNOWFLAKES CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: DRUNK UNI CYCLE
>> NO.
CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: DRUNK UNI CYCLE
>> NO.
CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: I BELIEVE I CAN FLY
>> NO.
CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: I BELIEVE I CAN FLY
I WANTED TO GO OUT ON A WINDOW
CHALLENGE.
IN THE R. KELLY STYLE.
I WANTED TO GO OUT ON A WINDOW
>> NO.
IN THE R. KELLY STYLE.
>> Jimmy: THE BOILING WATER
>> NO.
BUCKET CHALLENGE, THIS WOULD BE
>> Jimmy: THE BOILING WATER
FOR CHARITY, LIKE THE ICE BUCKET
BUCKET CHALLENGE, THIS WOULD BE
CHALLENGE BUT HOTTER.
FOR CHARITY, LIKE THE ICE BUCKET
>> NO.
CHALLENGE BUT HOTTER.
>> Jimmy: BORROW COPS' GUN
>> NO.
CHALLENGE?
>> Jimmy: BORROW COPS' GUN
>> NO.
CHALLENGE?
>> Jimmy: GRANDMA'S BEEN MISSING
>> NO.
FOR EIGHT SWEEKS CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: GRANDMA'S BEEN MISSING
>> NO.
FOR EIGHT SWEEKS CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: WHAT IF WE WANTED TO
>> NO.
FIND HER?
>> Jimmy: WHAT IF WE WANTED TO
>> THAT'S A PRETTY DARK PLACE.
FIND HER?
>> Jimmy: I FRAME MY MOM FOR
>> THAT'S A PRETTY DARK PLACE.
DRUG TRAFFICKING CHALLENGE.
>> Jimmy: I FRAME MY MOM FOR
>> YOU KNOW, I'M GOING TO TAKE
DRUG TRAFFICKING CHALLENGE.
THIS.
>> YOU KNOW, I'M GOING TO TAKE
>> Jimmy: THIS IS BULL
THIS.
[ BLEEP ].
>> Jimmy: THIS IS BULL
>> WE LIKE THE OTHER STUFF.
[ BLEEP ].
OKAY.
>> WE LIKE THE OTHER STUFF.
>> Jimmy: MAYBE I'LL START MY
OKAY.
OWN YOUTUBE.
>> Jimmy: MAYBE I'LL START MY
[ APPLAUSE ]
OWN YOUTUBE.
METUBE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
METUBE.
TONIGHT.
WE HAVE A GREAT SHOW FOR YOU
WE HAVE MUSIC FROM JUANES.
TONIGHT.
AND WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH
WE HAVE MUSIC FROM JUANES.
REGINA KING.
AND WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
REGINA KING.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Dicky: ABC'S JIMMY KIMMEL
♪ ♪
LIVE BROUGHT TO YOU BY T MOBILE.
.
♪
T-Mobile will do the math for
you.
Right now, when you join
T-mobile,
you get two lines of unlimited
with two of the latest phones
included
for just one hundred bucks a
month.
♪ ♪
Only TYLENOL® Rapid Release Gels
have laser drilled holes.
They release medicine fast,
for fast pain relief.
TYLENOL®
♪
Almost time for me to go.
Well, what if I...
drove me home?
[♪♪]
What if we lost track of time?
What if we took a leap of faith?
Whoo-hoo!
What if you...
missed my flight next week?
[♪♪]
The All-New RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
ThZ35K8Z Z16FZV4.
Y35K8Y Y16FY
Z35WHZ Z16FZ
Y35WHY Y16FY
♪ ♪
>> Jimmy: TONIGHT, YOU KNOW HIM
FROM MARVEL'S "THE PUNISHER" ON
NETFLIX, JON BERNTHAL IS HERE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HE PLAYS THE PUNISHER.
THEN, HIS SONG IS CALLED "LA
PLATA," JUANES FROM THE
MERCEDES-BENZ STAGE.
NEXT WEEK, CHRIS PINE WILL BE
HERE, DR. PHIL, MUSIC FROM BLACK
AND FLIPTON ARROW.
ON MONDAY IT WILL BE TWO YEARS
SINCE OUR PRESIDENT TOOK OFFICE.
AND WE WILL SALUTE AND PAY
TRIBUTE TO HIM WITH A
STAR-STUDDED MAGA-STRAVANGANZA.
"JIMMY KIMMEL LIVE INTERMISSION
ACCOMPLISHED! A HALFTIME TRIBUTE
TO TRUMP."
AND YOU'RE ALL INVITED.
THAT, I CAN TELL YOU.
THAT'S MONDAY NIGHT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
OUR FIRST GUEST TONIGHT IS A
VERY TALENTED ACTRESS WITH THREE
EMMYS AND A SHINY NEW GOLDEN
GLOBE AND CRITICS CHOICE AWARD
TO PROVE IT.
"IF BEALE STREET COULD TALK" IS
IN THEATRES NOW.
PLEASE WELCOME REGINA KING.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Jimmy: CONGRATULATIONS ON, ON
SO MANY AWARDS.
YOU ARE A FANTASTIC ACTRESS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jimmy: THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT
THAT.
AND I WILL TELL YOU, EVERY TIME
I SEE YOU IN SOMETHING, MY WIFE
AND I, WE HAVE A CONVERSATION
ABOUT WHAT A GREAT ACTRESS YOU
ARE.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
>> Jimmy: HOW MANY AWARDS HAVE
YOU WON FOR THIS MOVIE SO FAR?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT THE
NUMBER IS?
BECAUSE I HAVE A LIST.
>> DO YOU REALLY?
>> Jimmy: YES, IT'S A LONG LIST.
AND I MEAN, GOLDEN GLOBES,
CRITICS CHOICE, AUSTIN FILM
CRITICS, BOSTON ONLINE FILM
CRITICS, INDIANA, OKLAHOMA, THE
ONLINE CRITIC SOCIETY.
EVERY CITY YOU CAN IMAGINE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THE SATELLITE AWARDS.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW ABOUT SOME OF
THESE?
>> NO.
>> Jimmy: NO.
>> I MEAN I KNOW ABOUT THEM WHEN
THEY HAPPEN, BUT THIS WHOLE
AWARD SEASON THING HAS BEEN
QUITE, IT'S BEEN AN EDUCATION.
>> Jimmy: IN WHAT WAY HAS IT
BEEN AN EDUCATION?
>> FIRST OF ALL, I DIDN'T
REALIZE THERE WERE SO MANY FILM
CRITIC ASSOCIATION REVIEWS AND
ALL OF THAT.
>> Jimmy: RIGHT.
>> I HAD NO IDEA.
I THOUGHT THE FILM CRITICS,
THEY'RE THE CREW, THEY ARE AN
ALL TOGETHER.
>> Jimmy: ONE MASS.
>> NO, IT'S THE RANCHO CUCAMONGA
FILM CRITICS REVIEW IS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
EVERY SO OFTEN I GET JUST A CALL
FROM MY TEAM, AND I'M JUST
TICKLED AND AMAZED, BECAUSE I
DON'T KNOW ABOUT SOME OF THEM,
BUT I'M LIKE, THANK YOU.
>> Jimmy: AT THIS POINT YOU
PROBABLY HAVE TO GIVE SOME OF
THEM AWAY TO NEIGHBORS OR
SOMETHING, RIGHT?
>> NO!
THEY'RE MINE!
MY NAME, I'M GOING TO KEEP THEM
ALL.
>> Jimmy: EVEN THE OKLAHOMA FILM
CRITICS CIRCLE?
>> EVEN, BECAUSE THAT ONE,
OKLAHOMA?
>> Jimmy: THAT'S THE ONE, YEAH.
>> NEVER WOULD HAVE SAW THAT ONE
COMING.
>> Jimmy: ARE THERE ENOUGH FILM
CRITICS IN OKLAHOMA TO FORM A
CIRCLE?
>> I'M SURE THERE ARE ABOUT
EIGHT.
>> Jimmy: THERE ARE PROBABLY.
>> AT LEAST, AT LEAST.
>> Jimmy: WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jimmy: DO YOU RUN OUT OF
SPEECHES?
DO YOU RUN OUT OF THINGS TO SAY?
>> I HOPE NOT.
I HOPE TO CONTINUE TO BE ABLE TO
DO WORK THAT RECEIVES ACCOLADES,
BUT I JUST SAY A PRAYER AND JUST
MAKE, PLEASE, JUST DON'T LET ME
FLUB OR SAY SOMETHING SILLY.
>> Jimmy: DO YOU PLAN IT OUT
BEFOREHAND?
DO YOU WRITE SOMETHING DOWN
BEFORE YOU GO TO THE GOLDEN
GLOBES?
>> I DON'T, I FEEL LIKE I'M
JINXING THE WHOLE THING.
>> Jimmy: I THINK THAT'S TRUE.
THERE'S NOTHING MORE
EMBARRASSING THAN GETTING HOME
THAT NIGHT.
>> AND LOOKING AT THAT PAPER AND
GOING, YEAH.
>> Jimmy: YEAH, IT'S PREPARING
FOR FAILURE, YEAH.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
AND THERE'S ALWAYS SOMEONE YOU
FORGET.
>> Jimmy: YES, YOU HAVE TO
REMEMBER EVERYONE'S NAME.
>> OR YOU GET NAMES WRONG.
>> Jimmy: OH, HAVE YOU DONE
THAT?
>> I DID.
>> Jimmy: DO YOU THINK YOU NEED
TO THANK ANYONE WHOSE NAME YOU
DON'T KNOW HOW TO PRONOUNCE?
>> I SAY CALL THEM BY THEIR
FIRST NAME.
>> Jimmy: I SEE.
>> BECAUSE USUALLY THE LAST
NAMES ARE THE DOOZIES.
BUT I SAY JUST THE FIRST NAME.
>> Jimmy: THAT'S VERY, MOST
PEOPLE DON'T HAVE THIS PROBLEM.
YOU KNOW?
>> THEY CALL THEM CHAMPAGNE
PROBLEM, RIGHT?
>> Jimmy: HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
I SAW IT WAS YOUR BIRTHDAY ON
TUESDAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jimmy: DID THEY GIVE YOU
AWARDS FOR THAT, TOO?
OR DID YOU GET GIFTS?
OR WHAT DID YOU DO FOR YOUR
BIRTHDAY?
>> I DID, I DID.
I GOT A LOT OF LIQUOR.
>> Jimmy: DID YOU?
>> YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT SAYS
ABOUT ME.
>> Jimmy: PEOPLE GIVE YOU
BOTTLES?
>> YES, YES, NICE BOTTLES.
>> Jimmy: AND WHEN THEY GIVE IT
TO YOU, DO YOU OPEN IT UP RIGHT
AWAY AND ENJOY?
>> NO, I TAKE MY TIME.
I LIKE TO OPEN THEM UP WITH
PEOPLE.
>> Jimmy: DID YOU HAVE A PARTY
OR ANYTHING?
>> I DID NOT HAVE A PARTY.
I HAD A PARTY OF ONE AT THE SPA
FOR LIKE FOUR HOURS.
IT WAS SO SWEET, BECAUSE MY
MASSEUSE AS SHE WAS WALKING ME
IN, SHE GOES, I KNOW I'M NOT
SUPPOSED TO SAY THIS, BUT I'M
JUST SO HAPPY FOR YOU.
>> Jimmy: OH, REALLY?
>> IT WAS SO, THE AMOUNT OF LOVE
THAT I'M GETTING FROM PEOPLE.
>> Jimmy: YOU CAN THANK YOUR
MASSEUSE AT THE OSCARS.
DO YOU REMEMBER HER FIRST NAME?
>> NO.
>> Jimmy: I WANT TO THANK, I
WANT TO THANK MIRANDA FOR THE
DEEP TISSUE.
>> YES, YES.
YOU REALLY GOT UP IN THOSE
SHOULDERS.
>> Jimmy: YEAH, YOU MIGHT RUN
OUT OF PEOPLE TO THANK, WITH ALL
THESE AWARDS, IT'S CRAZY.
>> I DON'T THINK I'LL RUN OUT OF
PEOPLE TO THANK.
>> Jimmy: WHO ARE YOU EXCITED TO
MEET AT THE GOLDEN GLOBES?
>> THIS WHOLE AWARD SEASON
THING, YOU'RE SEEING A LOT OF
THE SAME PEOPLE, AND THEN YOU
ALSO SEE PEOPLE THAT YOU'RE A
HUGE FAN OF.
>> Jimmy: YEAH.
>> AND I NORMALLY DON'T GO UP TO
PEOPLE AND ASK TO TAKE PICTURES,
JUST BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE IF
THEY'RE NOT VERY NICE PEOPLE
THEN THEY'VE JUST DESTROYED
WHAT'S IN MY HEAD.
SO I DECIDED TO GO AGAINST
EVERYTHING THAT I KNOW, AND I
SAW SAM ELLIOT.
>> Jimmy: OH, SAM ELLIOT, YEAH.
OH, YOU LOVE SAM ELLIOT.
>> CAN YOU TELL?
>> Jimmy: YEAH, SAM ELLIOTT'S A
REAL SEX SYMBOL, KIND OF AN
UNDER THE RADAR SEX SYMBOL.
>> OH, MY GOD, I LOVE THAT MAN.
>> Jimmy: DID YOU TELL HIM THAT?
>> I DID.
>> Jimmy: WAS HE DELIGHTED?
>> HE WAS.
HE WAS SO CHARMING AND EVEN
BETTER THAN I THOUGHT HE WOULD
BE IN THE MOMENT.
AND THE MUSTACHE IS REAL!
>> Jimmy: OH, YEAH.
>> IT'S JUST LIKE, IT'S PERFECT.
AND, AND I JUST SAID, I LOVE
"ROADHOUSE."
>> Jimmy: THAT'S ONE, HUH?
>> MY SISTER AND I USED TO WATCH
"ROADHOUSE."
OH, MY GOD.
>> Jimmy: HOW OLD WERE YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW, WAY TO YOUNG TO
HAVE THE THOUGHTS THAT I HAD
ABOUT SAM ELLIOT.
>> Jimmy: OH, LOOKS LIKE SAM WON
A LITTLE SOMETHING THERE, TOO.
WHEN WE COME BACK WE'LL SEE A
CLIP FROM YOUR MOVIE.
IT'S CALLED "IF BEALE STREET
COULD TALK."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
[Woman 1]
Did you bokeh my child?
Um, uh, that was totally
unintentional.
[Woman 1]
Why do you hate Jacob?
[LAUGHS]
What?
No-look.
I can un-bokeh. See?
[Woman 2]
Bokeh, un-bokeh.
[Woman 1]
Wow.
What kind of person
bokehs a child?
[Woman 1]
I would never bokeh your child.
Just so you know.
I had a few good tricks to help
hide my bladder leak pad.
Like the old "tunic tug".
But Always Discreet
is less bulky.
And it really
protects.
'Cause it turns liquid to gel.
So I have nothing to hide.
Always Discreet.
Chili's 3 for $10 presents
our signature
sirloin steak.
Aged to perfection
and served with
a starter and drink
for just $10.
Out with the cousins
and Aunt Nancy,
who's politely described
as a "free spirit."
Together We Chili's.
As a fitness junkie,
I customize everything -
bike, wheels, saddle.
That's why I switched to
Liberty Mutual.
They customized my insurance, so
I only pay for what I need.
I insured my car,
and my bike.
My calves are custom too,
but I can't insure those...
which is a crying shame.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
DOES YOUR CUSTOMERS
CONNECTING TO THE WIFI
EVER SLOW DOWN YOUR BUSINESS?
YES, IT DOES SLOW THINGS DOWN.
AGGRAVATING.
IT'S A NIGHTMARE.
SO OUR GIG-SPEED
NETWORK IS FAST.
AND WE GO BEYOND FAST BY
MAKING IT EASY TO CREATE
SEPARATE NETWORKS FOR YOUR
BUSINESS AND YOUR CUSTOMERS
AND EVEN CONTROL HOW MUCH
BANDWIDTH EACH OF THOSE GETS.
SO YOUR BUSINESS
WON'T MISS A BEAT.
THIS IS A BIG GAME CHANGER.
THIS IS THE NEW WAVE, AND
WHOEVER DOESN'T GET ON,
I THINK THEY WOULD
BE LEFT BEHIND.
WIFI PRO RUNS ON THE
GIG-SPEED NETWORK.
PAY JUST $49.95 A MONTH
FOR FAST INTERNET
AND GET A $300 PREPAID CARD.
COMCAST BUSINESS.
BEYOND FAST.
[phone ringing]
Remember the way we
used to do things?
Hey man...
Like connect with friends?
Dig it!
Or get in shape?
Or sell a house
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
[crash]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
>>> A CHILD IS COMIN'.
>> YOU SEE YOUR GRANDCHILD.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU.
>> IT'S YOUR GRANDCHILD.
>> WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES IT MAKE
HOW HE GETS HERE?
THE CHILD AIN'T GOT NOTHING TO
DO WITH THAT.
AIN'T NONE OF US GOT NOTHING TO
>> Jimmy: THAT IS REGINA KING IN
DO WITH THAT.
"IF BEALE STREET COULD TALK".
>> Jimmy: THAT IS REGINA KING IN
IT IS IN THEATERS NOW.
"IF BEALE STREET COULD TALK".
THIS IS WRITTEN AND DIRECTED BY
IT IS IN THEATERS NOW.
BARRY JENKINS WHO DID
THIS IS WRITTEN AND DIRECTED BY
"MOONLIGHT".
BARRY JENKINS WHO DID
AND OBVIOUSLY WON THE ACADEMY
"MOONLIGHT".
AWARD FOR THAT.
AND OBVIOUSLY WON THE ACADEMY
WHEN YOU'RE PLAYING A MOM IN THE
AWARD FOR THAT.
'70s, DO YOU GET EXCITED ABOUT
WHEN YOU'RE PLAYING A MOM IN THE
THE HAIRSTYLE?
'70s, DO YOU GET EXCITED ABOUT
BECAUSE THERE ARE MANY.
THE HAIRSTYLE?
>> THERE ARE MANY.
BECAUSE THERE ARE MANY.
THERE ARE A LOT OF WAYS TO GO.
>> THERE ARE MANY.
I DO.
THERE ARE A LOT OF WAYS TO GO.
AND IT'S SO INTERESTING, BECAUSE
I DO.
THERE'S A WHOLE STORY.
AND IT'S SO INTERESTING, BECAUSE
>> AND I HOPE I CAN GET IT ALL
THERE'S A WHOLE STORY.
IN.
>> AND I HOPE I CAN GET IT ALL
I WANTED LIKE AN AFRO.
IN.
>> Jimmy: THAT'S WHAT I WOULD
I WANTED LIKE AN AFRO.
HAVE, TOO.
>> Jimmy: THAT'S WHAT I WOULD
>> AND BARRY'S LIKE, YEAH, NO.
HAVE, TOO.
>> Jimmy: WHY NO?
>> AND BARRY'S LIKE, YEAH, NO.
>> BUT, YOU KNOW, I'M NO LONGER
>> Jimmy: WHY NO?
LIKE DOING ANYTHING, LIKE
>> BUT, YOU KNOW, I'M NO LONGER
PRESSING MY HAIR OUT.
LIKE DOING ANYTHING, LIKE
I'VE GOT AN AFRO, BARRY, THAT
PRESSING MY HAIR OUT.
THE WORLD WANTS TO SEE.
I'VE GOT AN AFRO, BARRY, THAT
BUT HE WAS LIKE, I APPRECIATE
THE WORLD WANTS TO SEE.
THAT, BUT NO.
BUT HE WAS LIKE, I APPRECIATE
>> Jimmy: NO AFRO.
THAT, BUT NO.
>> AND SO HE REALLY STARTED
>> Jimmy: NO AFRO.
SENDING PICTURES OF WOMEN THAT
>> AND SO HE REALLY STARTED
HE FELT VISUALLY SHARON IS THE
SENDING PICTURES OF WOMEN THAT
ROLE THAT I PLAY, WOULD BE.
HE FELT VISUALLY SHARON IS THE
AND I GOT IT.
ROLE THAT I PLAY, WOULD BE.
IT MADE SENSE.
AND I GOT IT.
AND HIM SHARING THAT JUST TURNED
IT MADE SENSE.
INTO, IT MADE ME UNDERSTAND THE
AND HIM SHARING THAT JUST TURNED
CHARACTER.
INTO, IT MADE ME UNDERSTAND THE
>> Jimmy: YOU STARTED WITH THE
CHARACTER.
HAIR.
>> Jimmy: YOU STARTED WITH THE
>> STARTED WITH THE HAIR.
HAIR.
>> Jimmy: THAT'S SOMETHING ELSE.
>> STARTED WITH THE HAIR.
>> AND WORKED THE WAY ON DOWN.
>> Jimmy: THAT'S SOMETHING ELSE.
>> Jimmy: I WANT TO ASK YOU
>> AND WORKED THE WAY ON DOWN.
ABOUT SOMETHING YOU PROBABLY
>> Jimmy: I WANT TO ASK YOU
CAN'T TALK ABOUT AT ALL, WHICH
ABOUT SOMETHING YOU PROBABLY
IS "WATCHMAN" ON HBO.
CAN'T TALK ABOUT AT ALL, WHICH
THIS IS A SHOW LOOSELY BASED, WE
IS "WATCHMAN" ON HBO.
DON'T KNOW EXACTLY WHAT IT IS,
THIS IS A SHOW LOOSELY BASED, WE
BUT YOU DID THE LEFTOVERS WITH
DAYMON LINDLEOFF.
THAT'S A FANTASTIC SHOW.
AND ARE YOU THE ONLY PERSON FROM
THE LEFTOVERS THAT HE TOOK WITH
HIM TO "WATCHMAN"?
>> WELL.
>> Jimmy: YEAH.
YEAH.
>> YES.
>> Jimmy: WHAT CAN YOU TELL US
ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE UP TO ON THAT
SHOW?
ANYTHING?
CAN YOU TELL US WHICH CHARACTER
YOU PLAY?
>> I CAN TELL YOU THAT I'M A
WOMAN.
>> Jimmy: OKAY.
>> AND THAT I AM MAYBE SOMEWHAT
OF A BAD-ASS.
>> Jimmy: OKAY.
>> AND I MAY HAVE SOME SCENES
WITH SOME REALLY AWESOME ACTORS.
>> Jimmy: THAT'S IT, HUH?
CAN YOU TELL US ANY, ANYTHING
ABOUT THE STORY AND WHAT, IN
WHAT ERA IT WILL TAKE PLACE?
SORRY, THIS IS REAL NERD STUFF,
>> NO, BECAUSE THE FANS ARE
REAL.
>> Jimmy: MM-HM.
>> IF I JUST SAY THE WRONG BIT
OF ANYTHING, THEY WILL CRACK THE
CODE.
YOU'RE TRYING TO BAIT ME.
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> Jimmy: NO?
>> NO.
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN, NOT ON MY
WATCH.
>> Jimmy: NICELY DONE.
REGINA KING, "IF BEALE STREET
COULD TALK" THEATERS NOW.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪ ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que será, será ♪
♪ What will be, will be ♪
♪ Whatever will be, will be ♪
♪ Que será, seráaaaaa ♪
Son...
Legends tell of hidden world.
Home of the dragons.
It's your destiny to protect
them.
[ rousing music ]
It's you and me bud, always.
Yeah!
Why shop Marshalls?
Because...
Their prices will thrill you.
Whoo-hoo!
The brands will surprise you.
Mwah!
And every trip feels
like an instant victory.
Woman:
Marshalls.
Never boring.
Always surprising.
Woman:
Marshalls.
I AM TOTALLY BLIND.
AND NON-24 CAN MAKE ME SHOW UP
TOO EARLY... OR TOO LATE.
OR MAKE ME FEEL LIKE
I'M NOT REALLY "THERE."
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR,
AND CALL
844-234-2424.
I Hear it in the Background and
she's Watching too, saying
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
♪
[FRIEND]
I've never seen that before.
♪
I have...
Wow,
that's an aggressive yellow.
Pretty great, huh?
If you're a banana.
I find it very... appealing.
Kellogg's Raisin Bran
with Bananas.
Two scoops meet real
banana slices.
I've done a good job
of raisin ya.
(VO)
This is the Avery's.
This is the Avery's trying the
hottest new bistro.
Two scoops meet real
banana slices.
Wait...and the
hottest taqueria?
And the hottest...What are
those? Oh, pierogis?
And this is the Avery's
wondering if eating out
is eating into saving for
their first home.
This is JC...
(Team Member)
Welcome to Wells Fargo,
how may I help?
(VO)
who's here to help with a free
Financial Health Conversation,
no strings attached.
This is the Avery's with the
support they needed to get
back on track. Well done guys.
(Team Member)
This is Wells Fargo.
Before discovering Nexium 24HR
to treat his frequent heartburn,
Steven could only imagine
enjoying a spicy taco.
Now, his world
explodes with flavor.
Nexium 24HR stops
acid before it starts
for all-day all-night
protection.
Can you imagine 24-hours
without heartburn?
(Paul)
How do we tell people they get
the best of both worlds
with Sprint?
(Sassbot)
How about we get two-sport
legend, Bo Jackson...
(Bo)
Sup?
Guys - you don't need me.
Just tell people they get a
great network AND
a great price with Sprint.
(Sassbot)
Yes! You can get an Unlimited
plan and an iconic phone
for just $25 a month, on an LTE
advanced network that's
up to 2X faster than before.
(Evelyn)
Bo does...know.
(VO)
Switch to Sprint and get an
Unlimited plan with the
Samsung Galaxy S9 lease
and Hulu included
for just $25 a month.
No trade-in required.
For people with hearing loss,
visit Sprintrelay.com
Z35WDZ Z16FZ
Y35WDY Y16FY
>> Jimmy: WELCOME BACK.
JON BERNTHAL AND MUSIC FROM
JUANES IS ON THE WAY.
BUT FIRST, IT IS THIS WEEK IN
UNNECESSARY CENSORSHIP.
>> BRITAIN'S PRIME MINISTER
THERESA PAY [ BLEEP ]ED THE
BIGGEST [ BLEEP ] IN HISTORY.
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO STICK MY
[ BLEEP ] IN THAT MEAT GRINDER.
>> HE'S [ BLEEP ]ED HIM SEVERAL
TIMES.
>> DOES ANYBODY HERE NOT
[ BLEEP ] THEY ARE CHILDREN?
WOW.
THAT'S A LOT OF PEOPLE.
NOT ONE?
>> REMEMBER TWO THINGS.
NUMBER ONE, PLEASE [ BLEEP ] MY
[ BLEEP ].
NUMBER TWO.
I'M PROBABLY.
>> I WAS THE LAST ONE TO
[ BLEEP ] TODAY, AND NOW I AM
THE FIRST ONE TO [ BLEEP ]
TONIGHT.
IT FELT REALLY GOOD.
>> SO I WENT DOWN TO THE GROUND
AND [ BLEEP ] MY DOG.
>> DON'T INTERRUPT.
>> I REMEMBER MY FIRST TIME
BABYSITTING.
A 4-YEAR-OLD LOCKED ME IN THE
BATHROOM AND THE FIRE DEPARTMENT
HAD TO COME.
>> MY FIRST TIME, A KID STUCK A
[ BLEEP ] SO FAR UP HIS
[ BLEEP ] HE ENDED UP IN THE ER.
>> AH!
>> Jimmy: WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK
WITH JON BERNTHAL.
♪ ♪
of your ulcerative colitis
ke the treatment
in a different direction.
Talk to your doctor
about XELJANZ,
a pill, not an
injection or infusion,
for adults with moderate to
severe ulcerative colitis.
XELJANZ is the first and
only FDA-approved pill
for moderate to severe UC.
It can reduce symptoms
in as early as two weeks,
improve the appearance of
the intestinal lining,
and provide lasting
steroid-free remission.
XELJANZ can lower your
ability to fight infections
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened.
As have tears in the
stomach or intestines,
serious allergic reactions,
low blood cell counts,
higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels.
Don't start XELJANZ
if you have an infection.
Your doctor should
perform blood tests
before and while
taking XELJANZ,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if
you've been somewhere
fungal infections are common
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B or C, or
are prone to infections.
You could take your UC treatment
in a different direction.
Ask your gastroenterologist
about XELJANZ.
Sometimes the best time
is time you make for yourself.
AVEENO® Daily
Moisturizing Lotion
improves skin hydration
in just one day.
And for twice the moisture,
try the body wash too.
AVEENO®.
Naturally
Beautiful
Results®.
♪
Clean up your family's
trash talk
with the Glad Advanced
Protection kitchen bag.
It's Glad's strongest,
toughest,
most leak resistant bag.
Be happy, it's Glad.™
From the start, the C-Class
was ahead of its time.
Still, we never stopped
making it stronger.
Faster.
Smarter.
Because to be the best,
is to never ever stop
making it better.
The new 2019 C-Class Family.
Lease the C 300 Sport Sedan
for $429 a month
at your local
Mercedes-Benz dealer.
Mercedes-Benz.
The best or nothing.
Now you can make
any morning of the week
feel like the weekend.
With Jimmy Dean
Simple Scrambles.
Made fresh with two real eggs,
sausage 'n cheese.
And ready in seconds.
Why don't you put a
Sunday morning shine
on tomorrow morning's
breakfast.
♪ ♪
>> Jimmy: THOSE ARE FAKE.
STILL TO COME, MUSIC FROM
JUANES.
YOU KNOW OUR NEXT GUEST AS
ZOMBIE-KILLER-TURNED-ZOMBIE
SHANE ON "THE WALKING DEAD".
NOW HE IS SUPER VIGILANTE FRANK
CASTLE IN MARVEL'S "THE
PUNISHER".
SEASON TWO IS AVAILABLE TO
STREAM NOW ON NETFLIX.
PLEASE SAY HELLO TO JON
BERNTHAL.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Jimmy: HOW YOU DOIN',
EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
THE FAMILY GOOD?
>> THE FAMILY IS SO GOOD.
>> Jimmy: DO YOU BRING THE WHOLE
FAMILY TO NEW YORK WHEN YOU'RE
SHOOTING "THE PUNISHER"?
>> I BRING MY DOG FAMILY.
THE HUMANS STAY HOME.
>> Jimmy: THE HUMANS STAY HOME.
>> YEAH, THE BABIES STAY HOME,
BUT THE DOGS DEFINITELY COME.
WE HIGH TAIL IT ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
WE CAN'T PUT THEM ON PLANES, SO
WE DRIVE.
>> Jimmy: OH, YOU DO?
>> WE DO.
>> Jimmy: IS THAT FUN?
>> IT'S A MIXED BAG.
I DRIVE WITH MY OLD MAN.
>> Jimmy: YOU DO?
>> MY OLD MAN IS THE GREATEST ON
EARTH.
I LOVE MY DAD WITH ALL MY HEART.
RIGHT ON.
[ APPLAUSE ]
AND, YOU KNOW, FOR, FOR A
70-YEAR-OLD GUY TO JUST PICK UP
AND DRIVE ACROSS COUNTRY WITH
THREE PIT BULLS, THAT'S
SOMETHING, MAN.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU, THERE ARE
SPECIFIC RULES AND REGULATIONS
FOR DRIVING ACROSS COUNTRY WITH
MY OLD MAN.
FIRST OF ALL, YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO DO ANY DRIVING, WHICH IS
GREAT.
>> Jimmy: HE DRIVES THE WHOLE
TIME?
>> YOU AIN'T TOUCHIN' THE WHEEL,
WHICH IS COOL BECAUSE IT'S LIKE
HAVING A PERSONAL DRIVER, BUT
JIMMY, IF YOU EVEN THINK ABOUT
TURNING ON THAT RADIO.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHETHER IT'S
MUSIC OR NEWS, YOU WILL GET
SMACKED WITH THIS MAN HAND.
MY OLD MAN HAS THOSE THICK,
HAIRY, YOU TOUCH THAT DIAL, BAM!
THAT'S A DAY RUINER RIGHT THERE.
>> Jimmy: WHY DOES --
>> HE'S JUST GOT, HE'S VERY
SPECIFIC.
LOOK, WHEN YOU STOP FOR GAS,
THAT IS YOUR TIME TO GO TO THE
BATHROOM, TIME FOR THE DOGS TO
GO TO THE BATHROOM.
THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE GETTING YOUR
FOOD AND COFFEE.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT A STARBUCKS,
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
ALL OF A SUDDEN YOU'RE
HOLLYWOOD, MAN.
OH, MR. SOFT SERVE HOLLYWOOD
NEEDS A STARBUCKS.
AND YOU GET RIPPED APART.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M GETTING A
CARAMEL MACH YAW TOE.
I JUST WANT A BLACK COFFEE.
>> Jimmy: ARE YOU ABLE TO TALK
TO HIM IN THE CAR?
>> YES, YOU ARE.
I ALWAYS THINK WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE THESE DEEP FATHER-SON
BONDING MOMENTS.
WE START TO AT TIMES, BUT THE
THING IS, HE'S CONSTANTLY
SCREAMING AT EVERYONE ELSE ON
THE ROAD.
SAYING THINGS I DEFINITELY CAN'T
SAY HERE, BUT HE'S DRIVING WITH
HATRED, THE WHOLE ENTIRE WAY
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
IT INTERRUPTS THE MOMENT.
>> Jimmy: DOES YOUR DAD THINK
HE'S A GOOD ROAD TRIP PARTNER?
>> I THINK HE WOULD THINK HE'S
THE BEST.
HE DRIVES FASTER THAN HELL.
HE KNOWS HOW TO GO.
>> Jimmy: HOW MANY DAYS TO NEW
YORK?
>> YOU DO NOT STOP THAT MAN.
>> Jimmy: YOU DO TWO AND A HALF
DAYS OR SOMETHING?
>> YEAH.
>> Jimmy: WOW, MAYBE HE SHOULD
GET A JOB WITH UBER OR
SOMETHING.
SEEMS LIKE HE WOULD BE THE IDEAL
DRIVER.
>> JUST DON'T TOUCH THE RADIO,
MAN.
>> Jimmy: I KNOW ALL THIS STUFF
AND IT'S WORTHLESS INFORMATION,
BUT THE RARE MARVEL CHARACTER
WHO DOESN'T REALLY HAVE POWERS,
NECESSARILY, DO YOU FEEL CHEATED
IN ANY WAY ABOUT THAT?
>> I'M, LOOK, I LOVE FRANK
CASTLE, YOU KNOW, HE'S A
CHARACTER THAT HAS RESONATED
DEEPLY WITH THE MILITARY
COMMUNITY AND THE LAW
ENFORCEMENT COMMUNITY.
I WOULDN'T HAVE IT ANY OTHER
WAY.
>> Jimmy: DO YOU LOVE THOSE DAYS
WHEN YOU GET TO BEAT PEOPLE UP
ON SET?
IS THAT FUN?
>> TWO THINGS I'VE SWORN TO
MYSELF I WILL NEVER DO?
>> Jimmy: WHAT ARE THEY?
>> COME ON A SHOW LIKE THIS.
>> Jimmy: YOU'RE HERE.
>> COME ON A SHOW LIKE THIS AND
TALK ABOUT HOW I DO MY OWN
STUNTS OR HOW I GET INJURED
DOING STUNTS.
BUT I'M GOING TO DO BOTH THOSE
THINGS.
>> Jimmy: GO AHEAD.
>> I LIKE TO DO ALL MY OWN
STUNTS.
I LIKE TO DO ALL THE FIGHTING
MYSELF.
IT'S IMPORTANT FOR THE AUDIENCE
TO SEE FRANK CASTLE IN THOSE
MOMENTS.
AND I DID.
I BROKE MY HAND PRETTY BAD IN
THE FIRST FIGHT SCENE OF THE
SEASON.
>> Jimmy: OH, GREAT.
>> I KNEW EXACTLY WHEN IT
HAPPENED.
IT WAS A THREE-DAY FIGHT SCENE,
IT WAS THE FIRST DAY.
I'M A BOXER.
I KNEW EXACTLY IT WAS BROKEN.
BUT ME BEING AN ORANGUTAN I
DIDN'T WANT TO GET PULLED.
THE VERY NEXT THING I HAD TO DO
WITH A BROKEN HAND, MY MAN
JORDAN SCOTT, HE HAD TO BASH MY
BROKEN HAND INTO A TABLE.
AND I'M THE PUNISHER, MAN.
IT CAN'T JUST BE TWO HITS.
HE'S GOT TO BASH THE HELL OUT OF
MY HAND.
I SAY HEY, MAN IS THERE ANYWAY
WE COULD SWITCH IT TO THE LEFT
HAND?
HE'S LIKE NO, IT'S IN SCRIPT.
MAN UP.
NOW I'VE GOT TORN LIGAMENTS IN
MY HAND.
NEXT THING I DO IS KICK THIS
GUY'S LEG OUT AND I HAVE TO
CATCH HIM IN THIS POOR HAND.
AND I'M LIKE, IS THERE ANY
OPPORTUNITY TO MOVE THIS TO THE
OTHER HAND.
I SAID ALL RIGHT, THIS IS GOING
TO SUCK, HERE WE GO, TIMBER!
AND NOW I'VE DISLOCATED MY HAND.
AND THE VERY LAST THING WE HAD
TO DO IN THE SCENE ON DAY THREE
IS THESE GUYS ARE SHOOTING AT ME
WITH AUTOMATIC WEAPONS, AND I
THREW A BARSTOOL AT THEM.
I DIDN'T WRITE IT.
>> Jimmy: SIT ON THIS, NOW!
>> AND, YOU KNOW, I GO TO GRAB
THIS BARSTOOL, AND I JUST
FREEZE, BECAUSE I KNOW WHAT THIS
MANGLED MESS OF A HAND, I'M NOT
GOING TO BE ABLE TO THROW THE
STOOL.
STUNT COORDINATOR COMES UP AND
GOES COME ON, MAN, MAN UP.
>> Jimmy: YOU'RE NOT BEING
TREATED WELL.
>> NO, NO, HE'S THE BEST.
I SHOULD HAVE SAID SOMETHING.
THE DIRECTORS AND PRODUCERS ARE
ALL WATCHING TO SEE IN VIDEO
VILLAGE WATCHING THIS WAY.
AND I'M SUPPOSED TO THROW THAT
THING AT A MAT.
INSTEAD I JUST CHUCK THAT THING
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN YOU HEAR AH!
AND IT HIT THAT STUNT
COORDINATOR IN THE LEG.
AND HE HAS TO GO TO THE
HOSPITAL.
>> Jimmy: MAN UP.
HE WENT TO THE HOSPITAL.
ONE NON-PUNISHER RELATED
QUESTION FOR YOU.
>> WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
>> Jimmy: I READ, I THINK ON
MONDAY, AND THIS IS VERY
EXCITING.
DAVID CHASE IS GOING TO DO A
MOVIE, A PREQUEL TO THE
SOPRANOS, AND I READ THAT YOU
ARE GOING TO BE IN IT.
WILL YOU BE IN THIS FILM?
YOU DO KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT?
YOU'VE SEEN THE ARTICLE?
YOU'RE NODDING YES, DOES THAT
MEAN YES, I'M GOING TO BE IN
THIS FILM?
IT DOES MEAN YES.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I'M SORRY.
YES, YES.
>> Jimmy: WELL, IF YOU BREAK
ANYTHING ON THAT SET, PLEASE
TELL DAVID CHASE OR SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
>> I GIVE YOU MY WORD.
>> Jimmy: I THINK YOUR FATHER
MADE YOU SILENT ABOUT THINGS
THAT YOU SHOULDN'T BE.
IT'S GREAT TO SEE YOU, JON
BERNTHAL!
SEASON TWO OF "THE PUNISHER" IS
STREAMING NOW ON NETFLIX.
AND WE'LL RETURN WITH MUSIC FROM
JUANES.
>> Dicky: THE JIMMY KIMMEL LIVE
CONCERT SERIES IS PRESENTED BY
MERCEDES-BENZ.
THE BEST OR NOTHING.
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
>> Dicky: THE JIMMY KIMMEL LIVE
CONCERT SERIES IS PRESENTED BY
MERCEDES-BENZ.
THE BEST OR NOTHING.
>> Jimmy: I WANT TO THANK
REGINA KING AND JON BERNTHAL,
APOLOGIES TO MATT DAMON.
"NIGHTLINE" IS NEXT BUT FIRST,
HERE WITH HIS SONG, "LA PLATA,"
JUANES!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
♪ PARCE VENGA YO LE DIGO UNA
COSA HERMANO ESTO ES UN
VALLENATO ♪
♪ AY OMBE SE FUE LA PLATA QUEDÓ
LA PENA ♪ ♪ POR TANTA RUMBA PA'
OLVIDARTE YA NO HAY MANERA DE
CONSOLARME ♪
♪ SI NO ME DEJAS ENAMORARTE YA
NO HAY MANERA DE CONSOLARME SI
NO ME DEJAS ENAMORARTE ♪
♪ Y ESE BESITO QUE ME DISTE EN
LA BOCA ME TRAE LA MENTE LOCA ♪
♪ POR QUE TÚ CORAZÓN ES LIBRE Y
VIAJERO SI YO POR VOS ME MUERO ♪
♪ SI YO TE QUIERO CON EL ALMA SI
YO TE QUIERO HASTA LOS HUESOS ♪
♪ MI CORAZÓN NO ES SÓLO TUYO
PERO POR HOY YO TE LO PRESTO ♪
♪ ♪
♪ SI YO TE QUIERO CON EL ALMA SI
YO TE QUIERO HASTA LOS HUESOS ♪
♪ MI CORAZÓN NO ES SÓLO TUYO
PERO POR HOY YO TE LO PRESTO ♪
♪ DE COLOMBIA PARA EL MUNDO PAÁA
EHH OHH EHH OHH EHH OHH ♪
♪ LA LO A TI TE SACO UN RATO
RARO CARO Y NO BARATO POR TI
RESCATO UN GATO VOMITO FLOW EN
UN PLATO TU ♪
♪ TIENES ALGO KARDASHIAN QUE YO
TENGO ALGO DE MULATO ♪
♪ Y TENGO DE SUPERHÉROE LO QUE
JUANES DE VALLENATO AY NA' MAS
QUE QUIEREN LAS MUJERES ♪
♪ AY NA' MAS UN MOVIMIENTO PLEBE
AY NA' MAS Y TOME PA' QUE
LLEVE ♪
♪ Y TENGO DE SUPERHÉROE LO QUE
JUANES DE VALLENATO AY NA' MAS
QUE QUIEREN LAS MUJERES ♪
♪ AY NA' MAS UN MOVIMIENTO PLEBE
AY NA' MAS Y TOME PA' QUE
LLEVE ♪
♪ SI YO TE QUIERO CON EL ALMA SI
YO TE QUIERO HASTA LOS HUESOS ♪
♪ MI CORAZÓN NO ES SÓLO TUYO
PERO POR HOY YO TE LO PRESTO ♪
♪ SI YO TE QUIERO CON EL ALMA SI
YO TE QUIERO HASTA LOS HUESOS ♪
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]