>> Dicky: FROM HOLLYWOOD, IT'S
“JIMMY KIMMEL LIVE”!
TONIGHT --
DAVID SPADE, FROM THE SUPER BOWL
CHAMPION NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS,
SONY MICHEL, PART 4 OF “THE
MATCHELOR,” AND MUSIC FROM
MARGOT PRICE.
AND NOW, HEADING THIS WAY,
JIMMY KIMMEL!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> Jimmy: WELCOME.
HI, EVERYBODY.
THANKS FOR COMING.
VERY KIND.
I'M JIMMY, I'M THE HOST OF THE
SHOW.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
VERY NICE.
AND I WANT TO SAY --
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WELCOME, WELCOME TO THOSE OF YOU
VISITING.
WELCOME TO HOLLYWOOD, HOME OF
THE SUPER BOWL CHAMPION LOS
ANGELES RAMS.
[ CHEERS ]
DID THEY WIN?
I GOT BORED AND TURNED THE TV
OFF.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHAT IT GAME IT WASN'T.
IT WAS MORE AN ADEQUATE BOWL
THAN ANYTHING.
THE PATRIOTS BEAT THE RAMS 13-3,
WHICH 13-3 WAS ALSO ROB
GRONKOWSKI'S BLOOD ALCOHOL
CONTENT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THIS WAS THE LOWEST-SCORING GAME
IN SUPER BOWL HISTORY.
THE MOST DRAMATIC MOMENT OF THE
NIGHT CAME BETWEEN HARRISON FORD
AND A DOG.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THE GAME WAS SO SLOW THE
PATRIOTS DUMPED GATORADE ON BILL
BELICHICK JUST TO WAKE HIM UP.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THIS WAS THE PATRIOTS' SECOND
TIME IN THREE YEARS.
TOM BRADY BECAME THE FIRST
PLAYER TO WIN SIX NFL TITLES.
RAMS FANS DIDN'T HAVE A LOT TO
CHEER ABOUT.
BUT THE TEAM DID SET TWO SUPER
BOWL RECORDS, INCLUDING MOST
CONSECUTIVE PUNTS TO START A
GAME, WITH EIGHT.
FOR THOSE WHO ADMIRE THE
ARTISTRY OF PUNTING IT WAS, IS
QUITE AN EVENING.
RAMS HAD THE FIRST MALE CHEER
LEADERS IN SUPER BOWL HISTORY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I DON'T KNOW IF IT WORKED.
THEY ONLY SCORED THREE POINTS,
SO THANKS, MALE CHEERLEADERS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT WAS A TOUGH LOSS FOR THE RAMS
BUT THEY'RE A YOUNG TEAM, AN
EXCITING TEAM WITH A VERY BRIGHT
FUTURE, A GREAT YOUNG COACH.
IF OFFENSIVE LINEMAN ANDREW
WHITWORTH IS ANY INDICATION --
>> DON'T FEEL SORRY FOR MYSELF.
I REALIZE WHAT THIS GAME MEANS
ARE I CHESHIRE THE CRAP OUT OF
IT.
I DON'T GIVE A CRAP IF YOU'VE
GOT A HALL OF FAME BUST, A PRO
BOWLER, WIN 20 SUPER BOWLS, AT
THE END OF THE DAY YOU'RE ALL
GOING TO DIE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> Jimmy: THAT'S A DARK WAY OF
LOOKING AT IT.
I MEAN, I GET KEEPING IT REAL
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO KEEP THAT
IT REAL, YOU KNOW?
[ LAUGHTER ]
THAT HALFTIME SHOW LAST NIGHT,
IT REMINDED ME OF A SWEET 16
PARTY FOR THE DAUGHTER OF A
SAUDI ARABIAN PRINCE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT WAS WEIRD.
SOMEHOW THEY MANAGED TO FIND THE
ONLY WHITE DRUMLINE IN THE WHOLE
CITY OF ATLANTA.
AND MAROON 5, WHO ELSE, BIG BOI,
TRAVIS SCOTT, AND SPONGEBOB
PERFORMED TOGETHER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THE CROWDS AT THESE SUPER BOWL
GAMES, THIS CLIP OF ADAM LEVINE
SINGING KIND OF TELLS YOU ALL
YOU NEED TO KNOW, LOOK AT THIS.
♪
WATCH IN THE RIGHT-HAND CORNER.
YES.
[ LAUGHTER ]
MR. AND MRS. LEVINE REALLY
GETTING A KICK OUT OF -- LIKE A
CYALIS COMMERCIAL COME TO LIFE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
GOOD TIMES AT THE RADISSON
ATLANTA LAST NIGHT.
THERE WAS A WARDROBE MALFUNCTION
AT THE HALFTIME SHOW.
THE MALFUNCTION WAS SOMEONE IN
THE WARDROBE DEPARTMENT LET ADAM
LEVINE GO ON STAGE DRESSED LIKE
THIS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
GOLD CHAINS AND A DUNKIN' DONUT
TRACK SUIT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
PEOPLE ONLINE NEEDLESS TO SAY
HAD A LOT TO SAY ABOUT THE SHIRT
ADAM WAS WEARING UNDER THAT
JACKET.
HEATHER WROTE, WHEN ADAM LEVINE
MATCHES YOUR THROW PILLOWS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
KIM WROTE, I HAVE THE SAME LOOK
IN A CHAIR.
[ LAUGHTER ]
FROM JENNA, LEVINE-ESQUE DUR
TANS.
AND MORGAN WRITES, Y'ALL, AS
SOON AS I SAW ADAM LEVINE'S
SHIRT, I SAID IT LOOKED LIKE
SOME '70s HOME DECOR AND
FACEBOOK BACKED ME UP.
I WATCHED THE GAME YESTERDAY AT
MY FRIEND ADAM'S HOUSE WITH
HARD-CORE PATRIOTS FANS.
THESE ARE GUYS THE LAST TIME THE
PATRIOTS WON WERE JUMPING ON THE
COUCH AND TURNING THINGS OVER.
THIS YEAR THEY WON, I DON'T
KNOW, MAYBE THEY'RE EXHAUSTED
FROM THE RED SOX?
NOBODY SEEMED TO CARE THAT MUCH.
THEY'RE LIKE, OKAY, THAT WAS
NICE, I THINK I'LL HEAD HOME
NOW.
DICKY, HAVE BOSTON FANS
OFFICIALLY WON TOO MANY GAMES
NOW?
>> Dicky: I'LL TAKE ANOTHER ONE.
>> Jimmy: YOU'D TAKE ANOTHER
ONE.
>> Dicky: YEAH.
>> Jimmy: YOU'LL TAKE IT
QUIETLY, WITHOUT ZEAL?
>> Dicky: WITH DIG NIGHT.
>> Jimmy: DIGNITY.
RAMS FANS ARE A LITTLE OFF TOO.
RAMS HAVE ONLY BEEN IN L.A. FOR
THREE YEARS SINCE COMING BACK
FROM ST. LOUIS.
LIKE WHEN DAD MOVES BACK IN THE
HOUSE AFTER A DIVORCE.
THERE'S A PERIOD OF UNEASE.
YOU DON'T KNOW IF HE'S GOING TO
STAY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
JUST TO GIVE YOU A SENSE OF THE
RAMS FEVER THAT WAS REALLY JUST
HEATING THIS CITY UP, WE WENT
OUT ON THE STREET AND WE ASKED
PEOPLE TODAY TO CONGRATULATE THE
RAMS ON THEIR SUPER BOWL VICTORY
YESTERDAY.
[ AUDIENCE MOANING ]
IN TONIGHT'S BAD WEATHER FAN
EDITION OF "LIE WITNESS NEWS."
>> WHERE WERE YOU WHEN YOU FOUND
OUT THE RAMS WON?
>> I ACTUALLY WAS RIGHT HERE ON
HOLLYWOOD BOULEVARD.
WHEN I FOUND OUT THAT THE RAMS
WON.
>> WHERE'D YOU HEAR IT?
>> PEOPLE WAS TALKING ABOUT IT
IN FRONT OF THE DOLBY THEATER
WHAT WERE THEY SAYING?
>> THEY WERE SAYING LIKE, IT'S
KIND OF COOL THAT THE RAMS WON,
LIKE THAT WAS THEIR TEAM, SOME
PEOPLE LIKE, THEY SUCK.
>> WHAT WAS THE REACTION LIKE IN
L.A. WHEN THEY WON THE SUPER
BOWL LAST NIGHT?
>> IT WAS -- IT WAS LOUD.
IT WAS PASSIONATE.
AND IT WAS -- IT WAS INTENSE.
>> PASSIONATE HOW?
>> THERE WAS JUST A LOT OF
FEELINGS, AND LIKE -- KIND OF
LIKE RAGE INVOLVED.
>> RAGE?
>> YEAH.
>> ALMOST AS IF THEY LOST?
>> ALMOST AS IF THEY LOST.
>> WERE YOU ROOTING FOR THE
RAMS?
>> THE RAMS.
>> WERE YOU EXCITED WHEN THEY
WON?
>> YEAH, IT WAS GOOD.
>> CAN YOU DESCRIBE IT TO ME?
>> SITTING AT THE BAR, WATCHING
THE GAME.
WHEN THE FINAL CLOCK RAN OUT,
HEY.
TEXTED MY DAD, TELLS ME HE OWES
ME 10 BUCKS.
>> YOU TEXTED HIM?
>> YEAH.
>> CAN I SEE THE TEXT?
>> THE PHONE'S ABOUT TO DIE.
>> WHERE'S THE BATTERY OUT?
>> 64 RIGHT NOW.
>> IT'S NOT GOING TO DIE, THEN.
>> YEAH.
MIGHT TAKE ME AWHILE TO FIND IT,
MY PHONE'S KIND OF WONKY RIGHT
NOW.
>> WHAT DID YOU THINK OF THE
CONTROVERSIAL DORASIL AD WITH
O.J. IN IT?
>> ABOUT THE COMMERCIAL WITH
DURACELL, I DON'T HAVE AN
OPINION.
SOME PEOPLE MIGHT THINK IT WAS
FUN, SOME PEOPLE MIGHT THINK
IT'S NOT OKAY.
IN THE END IT PROBABLY STAY IN
YOUR MIND.
WE WILL REMEMBER IT SOMEHOW.
SO I THINK THAT'S THE POINT OF A
COMMERCIAL.
>> WHEN HE KILLS THE ENERGIZER
BUN THOUGH?
>> YEAH, WHEN HE KILLS THE
BUNNY.
IT STAYS IN YOUR MIND.
>> WE'RE GOING TO DO JUST THE
FIGHT SONG REALLY QUICK.
♪ WE ARE THE RAMS AND WE'RE
GOING TO THE SUPER BOWL ♪
♪ AND WE'RE GOING TO WIN AND
WE'RE ALSO GOING TO ♪
>> CONGRATULATIONS TO THE RAMS
ON YOUR VICTORY.
>> YOU DID A GREAT GAME, KEEP
DOING THAT, AND GOOD LOOK.
>> GOOD JOB, THE RAMS, I'M GLAD
YOU BEAT THE PATRIOTS BECAUSE NO
ONE LIKES THEM.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, RAMS, ON
YOUR SUPER BOWL VICTORY.
WE KNEW TOM BRADY WAS GOING TO
LOSE BECAUSE HE CHEATS AND
THAT'S WHAT CHEATERS DO, THEY
LOSE.
>> AWESOME, CONGRATULATIONS.
WAIT.
THE RAMS DIDN'T WIN THE SUPER
BOWL.
>> Jimmy: OH.
OH, WE FOUND ONE GUY ON THE
STREET.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SO THE PRESIDENT, BY THE WAY,
HAD A BIG SUPER BOWL PARTY AT
MAR-A-LAGO, HIS CLUB IN PALM
BEACH, FLORIDA.
BEFORE THE GAME TRUMP SAT FOR A
WIDE-RANGING INTERVIEW WITH CBS
DURING WHICH HE LASHED OUT AT
OUR OLD ENEMIES FROM ABOVE.
>> AND I SAID TO CANADA, LOOK,
WE HAVE A GREAT AMERICAN COMPANY
KNOWN AS THE NFL.
AND THEY WERE BEING HURT AND
TREATED UNFAIRLY, THE NFL, BY
CANADA, FOR A LONG TIME.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Jimmy: HE CALLED CANADA AND
SAID, HEY, CANADA, STOP BEING
MEAN TO FOOTBALL, WILL YOU?
[ LAUGHTER ]
THEN HE WEIGHED IN ON THE
POSSIBILITY OF GETTING
IMPEACHED.
>> ARE YOU PREPARED FOR AN
ATTEMPT TO IMPEACH YOU?
>> THE ONLY WAY THEY CAN WIN,
BECAUSE THEY CAN'T WIN THE
ELECTION, IS TO BRING OUT THE
ARTIFICIAL WAY OF IMPEACHMENT.
AND THE PROBLEM IS YOU CAN'T
IMPEACH SOMEBODY FOR DOING THE
BEST JOB OF ANY PRESIDENT IN THE
HISTORY OF OUR COUNTRY FOR THE
FIRST TWO YEARS.
>> Jimmy: HE GOT US ON A
TECHNICALITY.
DOES HE KNOW THAT LINCOLN SIGNED
THE EMANCIPATION PROCLAMATION IN
HIS FIRST TWO YEARS AS
PRESIDENT?
HE PROBABLY DOES.
IN ANY EVENT, THE PRESIDENT HAD
A FUN WEEKEND.
HE EVEN PLAYED A ROUND OF GOLF
WITH JACK NICKLAUS AND TIGER
WOODS.
I FEEL THESE TWO TWEETS BACK TO
BACK SUM THE TRUMP PRESIDENCY UP
MORE THAN ANY HISTORY BOOK EVER
WILL.
FIRST THE LEGEND OF BAGGER VANCE
WROTE, EVERYONE IS ASKING HOW
TIGER PLAYED YESTERDAY, THE
ANSWER IS, GREAT, TWONG,
STRAIGHT, AND PUTTED
FANTASTICALLY WELL, HE SHOT A
64, TIGER IS BACK AND WILL BE
WHEN WINNING MAJORS AGAIN.
NOT SURPRISINGLY JACK ALSO
PLAYED REALLY WELL, HIS PUTTING
IS AMAZING, JACK AND TIGER LIKE
EACH OTHER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THEN AN HOUR LATER, WITH
CARAVANS MARCHING THROUGH MEXICO
AND TOWARD OUR COUNTRY,
REPUBLICANS MUST BE PREPARED TO
DO WHATEVER IS NECESSARY FOR
STRONG BORDER SECURITY, DEMS DO
NOTHING.
IF THERE IS NO WALL THERE IS NO
SECURITY.
HUMAN TRAFFICKING, DRUGS, AND
CRIMINALS OF ALL DIMENSIONS KEEP
OUT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IS ANYONE MONITORING HIS BLOOD
SUGAR?
[ LAUGHTER ]
PUT THE GOLF TWEET BACK UP
THERE.
THIS WAS MY FAVORITE PART, JACK
AND TIGER LIKE EACH OTHER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THAT WOULD MAKE A GREAT TITLE
FOR A CHILDREN'S BOOK.
"JACK AND TIGER LIKE EACH
OTHER."
BY DONALD J. TRUMP.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
PAGE 9, HIS PUTTING IS AMAZING.
I DON'T WANT TO RUIN THE ENDING
BUT THE ORANGE GUY WINS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
MEANWHILE, WHILE TRUMP'S ON THE
GOLF COURSE, A LOT OF AMERICA IS
STILL REELING FROM THE COLD.
THIS IS SOMETHING FOR THOSE OF
YOU WHO FIND YOURSELVES STUCK AT
HOME BECAUSE OF THE WINTER
WEATHER, IT'S OUR LATEST YOUTUBE
CHALLENGE.
THE CHALLENGE IS COOK UP A PLATE
OF SPAGHETTI, CALL YOUR FAMILY
OR FRIENDS OR ROOMMATES IN FOR
DINNER, PUT A BIG SNOWBALL ON
THE PLATE NEXT TO THE SPAGHETTI.
RECORD THEM AND UPLOAD IT TO
YOUTUBE WITH, HEY, JIMMY KIMMEL,
I MADE SPAGHETTI AND SNOWBALLS.
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO WE
ENCOURAGED PEOPLE TO SERVE
SNOWBALLS IN BED AND THAT WENT
LIKE THIS.
>> JIMMY KIMMEL MADE ME DO IT!
>> Jimmy: MATTHEW IS STILL
GROUNDED, BY THE WAY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THAT'S HEY, JIMMY KIMMEL, I MADE
SPAGHETTI AND SNOWBALLS.
LOOK FOR A MESSAGE FROM US AND
WE'LL PUT THE BEST ONES ON THE
SHOW.
TONIGHT ON ABC, BY THE WAY, WE
HAD A NEW EPISODE OF "THE
BACHELOR" WHICH IS BIGGER THAN
THE SUPER BOWL.
THERE'S A YOUNG WOMAN ELEASE ON
THE BACHELOR WHO TONIGHT PROVED
HERSELF TO BE SIMULTANEOUSLY THE
SMARTEST AND DUMBEST CONTESTANT
IN "BACHELOR" HISTORY.
>> I WANT THE TIME AND ATTENTION
THAT A RELATIONSHIP DESERVES.
I CAN'T -- I MEAN, LIKE --
LITERALLY CAN'T ACCEPT A
PROPOSAL AFTER A FEW MONTHS OF
SHARING YOUR TIME AND ATTENTION
WITH OTHER PEOPLE.
I CAN'T DO IT.
>> Jimmy: HE'S LIKE, WELL --
THAT MAKES SENSE BUT THAT'S KIND
OF THE IDEA OF THE SHOW.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT'S AN ENGAGEMENT RING GAME
SHOW.
SEE, THIS IS WHY IT'S SO
IMPORTANT TO READ THE "TV GUIDE"
DESCRIPTION OF A PROGRAM BEFORE
YOU GO ON IT.
SO COLTON WENT ON A ONE ON ONE
WITH HEATHER.
IF YOU FOLLOW THE SHOW, A
23-YEAR-OLD WOMAN WHO'S NEVER
KISSED ANYONE.
THAT IS, UNTIL TONIGHT.
SHE GOT A ROSE AND HER FIRST
KISS AS FIREWORKS EXPLODED
AROUND HER AND COLTON.
DURING THE DAY COLTON ASKED
ABOUT HER PAST RELATIONSHIPS.
SHE CLAIMED TO HAVE DATED A GUY
FOR EIGHT MONTHS.
A GUY SHE NEVER KISSED AND HE
NEVER TRIED TO KISS HER.
WHICH, I DON'T KNOW, GOING OUT
WITH AN ADULT MAN FOR EIGHT
MONTHS AND NOT EVER KISSING HIM
ISN'T CALLED DATING, IT'S CALLED
MAKING A GAY BEST FRIEND.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT'S A DIFFERENT THING.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I HAVE MY OWN BACHELOR SPINOFF
SHOW.
I'VE BEEN LENDING MATCHMAKING
SERVICE TO A FORMER "BACHELOR"
CONTESTANT, DANIELLE M., ON THE
NICK VIALLS SEASON OF "THE
BACHELOR,," THEN "BACHELOR IN
PARADISE."
SHE FOUND LOVE ON NEITHER OF
THOSE SHOWS.
I SIGNED DANIELLE UP WITH TINDER
TO SEE WHO WE COULD MEET FOREHER
AND TONIGHT WE MET CALEB.
>> PREVIOUSLY MY SKILLS BROUGHT
US TO BRIAN.
>> HI.
>> WHO APPEARED TO MEASURE UP.
>> I'M TALL AND HE'S TALL.
>> I MADE MY MOVE.
>> GOOD NEWS ACTION WE'RE
INTERESTED IN YOU.
>> BRIAN SEEMED INTO US.
>> THIS IS ABSOLUTELY THE
WEIRDEST FIRST DATE I'VE EVER
HAD FOR SURE.
>> NOW IT'S TIME FOR OUR FINAL
LEG OF THIS TINDER TRIATHLON.
SO WHAT ELSE DO WE HAVE HERE?
>> CALEB.
HE'S 26.
>> HE'S YOUNG.
>> YEAH.
>> HE'S 26.
>> CINEMATOGRAPHER.
>> YEAH.
>> YES.
>> CINEMATOGRAPHER.
>> THERE HE IS WITH A WOMAN.
>> YES.
I HOPE THAT'S NOT HIS WIFE.
>> THERE HE IS WITH A WOMAN.
>> YEAH.
I HOPE THAT'S NOT HIS WIFE.
BECAUSE I'M DEFINITELY NOT INTO
>> YEAH.
THAT.
BECAUSE I'M DEFINITELY NOT INTO
>> YOU'RE NOT INTO THAT.
THAT.
THIS IS HOPEFULLY HIS SISTER,
>> YOU'RE NOT INTO THAT.
MAYBE?
THIS IS HOPEFULLY HIS SISTER,
>> LET'S HOPE SO.
MAYBE?
>> SHE KIND OF LOOKS LIKE HIM.
>> LET'S HOPE SO.
>> OKAY.
>> SHE KIND OF LOOKS LIKE HIM.
>> LET'S FIND OUT.
>> OKAY.
HI!
OH, HE'S ON THE PHONE.
>> HE'S CALLING HIS LAWYER.
>> COOL, HI, LET ME CALL YOU
BACK IN A BIT.
HELLO, HI, EVERYBODY.
>> HI, CALEB.
>> I'M CALEB, 92 US TO MEET YOU.
>> I'M JIMMY.
>> MY FRIEND JIMMY.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> HELLO, EVERYBODY.
>> THESE PEOPLE AREN'T WITH US.
>> MY NAME IS CALEB AND I AM
FROM MASSACHUSETTS BUT I'M
LIVING IN L.A. RIGHT NOW AS A
CINEMATOGRAPHER.
>> WE SAW YOU ON TINDER.
>> YOU GUYS WERE ON TINDER
TOGETHER?
>> YEAH.
>> NICE.
>> KIND OF A THREESOME IN A WAY.
>> DUDE, I'M DOWN.
>> YOU'RE A YOUNG GUY.
WHAT WAS THE LAST SERIOUS
RELATIONSHIP YOU HAD?
>> OH, MAN.
>> HAVE YOU HAD ONE?
>> YEAH.
NO, I WAS DATING THIS WOMAN.
I WAS 23, SHE WAS IN HER EARLY
30s.
>> OKAY.
>> SHE TAUGHT YOU THE WAYS OF
LOVE?
>> IS THAT THE GIRL ON YOUR
PROFILE?
>> OH -- THAT'S MY COUSIN.
>> OH ACTION OKAY, YEAH.
>> SEE THAT?
>> YOU WERE RIGHT.
>> YOU'RE CLOSE WITH THE FAMILY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT LIKE
CHILDREN AND MARRIAGE AND THAT
SORT OF THING?
>> UM -- I THINK THAT, YEAH,
IT'S --
>> HOW FAR OUT DO YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU ARE FROM THAT?
>> YOU KNOW, I --
>> CAN I GET A SAMPLE OF YOUR
SPERM BEFORE YOU LEAVE?
>> I WOULDN'T GO THAT FAR.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL.
>> OH MY GOD.
THIS IS GOING TO BE THE DEATH OF
ME.
>> DANIELLE, YOU HAVE A
QUESTION, RIGHT?
AN IMPORTANT QUESTION.
DO YOU PAY FOR YOUR OWN NETFLIX
ACCOUNT?
>> OR DO YOU MOOCH OFF SOMEONE
ELSE?
>> OF COURSE I MOOCH OFF SOMEONE
ELSE, YOU DON'T?
>> OH!
NEXT!
>> I STOLE MY COLLEGE ROOMMATE'S
HBO PASSWORD.
BUT BEYOND THAT, NETFLIX FROM MY
PARENTS, I NEVER REALLY STOLE
ANYTHING.
MAYBE A PACK OF GUM WHEN I WAS
REALLY YOUNG.
>> HOW MANY WOMEN HAVE YOU DATED
ON TINDER?
>> I'VE ONLY MET UP WITH ONE
OTHER WOMAN.
>> DID SHE BRING A TALK SHOW
HOST TO THE DATE?
>> SHE DID NOT.
>> OKAY.
>> THIS IS A DEFINITE PLUS FOR
DANIELLE.
>> THIS IS A FIRST.
>> YEAH.
>> WE'RE GOING TO THINK ABOUT
YOU, AND YOU THINK ABOUT
DANIELLE.
>> YEAH, MULL THE SITUATION
OVER.
>> WE'LL SEE WHAT WE THINK.
>> NOW I HAVE TO LEAVE?
>> YES.
YOU HAVE TO LEAVE NOW.
>> Jimmy: NEXT TIME ON "THE
MATCHELOR."
IT'S DECISION TIME FOR DANIELLE
M.
WILL SHE FIND LOVE?
WHO WILL SHE CHOOSE?
AND WHY IS SHE SMELLING HER
PHONE?
ALL THESE QUESTIONS WILL BE
ANSWERED NEXT TIME ON THE MOST
EXCITING DRAMATIC, SHOCKING,
AMAZING, SHOCKING AND AMAZING
MATCHELOR LIVE FINALE RESULT
SHOW EVER, BECAUSE IT'S THE
FIRST ONE, AND PROBABLY THE
LAST.
ALL THIS NEXT MONDAY ON "THE
MAT
MATCHELOR."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> Jimmy: THAT'S RIGHT, THAT'S
NEXT WEEK.
AHEAD ON THE SHOW, MUSIC FROM
MARGOT PRICE, SUPER BOWL
CHAMPION SONY MICHEL IS HERE.
BE RIGHT BACK WITH DAVID SPADE.
Almost time for me to go.
Well, what if I...
drove me home?
[♪♪]
What if we lost track of time?
What if we took a leap of faith?
Whoo-hoo!
What if you...
missed my flight next week?
[♪♪]
The All-New RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
The All-New RAV4.
(ding)
Hey, who are you?
Oh, hey Jeff, I'm a car thief...
What?!
I'm here to
steal your car because,
well, that's my job.
What?
What??
WHAT?!
(laughing)
What??
WHAT?!
What?!
[crash]
WHAT?!
Haha, it happens.
And if you've got
cut-rate car insurance,
paying for this could
feel like getting robbed twice.
So get Allstate...
and be better protected
from Mayhem...
like me.
♪
What??
Wait!
First they're Sour.
Then they're Sweet.
For me?
♪
Yeahh!
SOUR PATCH Kids.
Sour. Sweet. Gone.
♪ If you love me, love me,
love me like you say ♪
♪ Darling, tell me
all the ways ♪
♪ Tell me all the ways ♪
♪ All the ways ♪
At the store, or to your door.
Target Run and Done.
Hey, Darryl.
Would you choose the network
rated #1 in the nation
by the experts,
or the one awarded
by the people?
Uh...
Correct! You don't
have to choose,
'cause, uh...
Oh!
(VO)
Switch to the network awarded
by RootMetrics
and J.D. Power.
Now get $300 off
our best phones.
ONEEEEE...
DID YOU TRY THIS ONE?
FEEL THIS ONE. IT'S AMAZING!
TWOOOOO...
IT'S NICE. BUT
IT'S KINDA PRICEY.
HI.
YOU CAN'T SKIMP ON A
DECISION THIS IMPORTANT.
A MATTRESS IS WHERE YOU'LL
SPEND OVER HALF YOUR LIFE
AND EAT ALL YOUR MEALS.
BUT IT'S ALL GOOD.
JUST USE PAY IT PLAN IT.
PAY IT PLAN IT IS A PAYMENT
FEATURE FROM AMERICAN EXPRESS.
CHOOSE A MONTHLY PLAN TO SPLIT
UP LARGE PURCHASES OVER TIME
WITH NO INTEREST
AND A FIXED FEE.
NEED ME TO HELP YOU CARRY
THIS TO YOUR CAR OR...
THE POWERFUL BACKING
OF AMERICAN EXPRESS.
DON'T LIVE LIFE WITHOUT IT.
>> Jimmy: HI THERE, WELCOME BACK
FROM THE SHOW.
.
TONIGHT, FROM THE SUPER BOWL
CHAMPION NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS,
HE IS A ROOKIE WHO SCORED THE
ONLY TOUCHDOWN IN THE GAME.
SONY MICHEL IS HERE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THEN, SHE IS A GRAMMY NOMINEE
FOR BEST NEW ARTIST.
HER ALBUM IS CALLED “ALL
AMERICAN MADE.”
MARGO PRICE FROM THE
MERCEDES-BENZ STAGE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YOU CAN SEE MARGO PRICE ON TOUR
WITH CHRIS STAPLETON STARTING
JULY 9 IN THE ALLENTOWN,
PENNSYLVANIA.
TOMORROW NIGHT WE HAVE A SPECIAL
SHOW.
OUR "STATE OF THE UNION RESULTS
SHOW."
WE WILL TRY TO MAKE SENSE OF
WHATEVER THE PRESIDENT HAS TO
SAY WITH WILL ARNETT,
PRESIDENTIAL HOPEFUL
JULIÁN CASTRO, AND MUSIC FROM
RANDY HAUSER, AND LATER THIS
WEEK, DANIEL RADCLIFFE,
JENNIFER CONNELLY,
PHOEBE ROBINSON, OSCAR NOMINEE
RICHARD E. GRANT, PLUS MUSIC
FROM WHY DON'T WE, AND LAUV AND
TROYE SIVAN.
SO PLEASE JOIN US FOR ALL OF
THAT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OUR FIRST GUEST HAD A VERY BUSY
WEEKEND.
HE WAS AT THE SUPER BOWL IN
ATLANTA, THEN HAD TO RUSH BACK
TO L.A. IN TIME TO WATCH "THE
BACHELOR" TONIGHT.
HIS MOVIE, “THE WRONG MISSY”
WILL AIR LATER THIS YEAR ON
NETFLIX.
PLEASE WELCOME DAVID SPADE.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> OH, YEAH.
>> Jimmy: VERY GOOD TO SEE YOU,
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
>> THANKS, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
I'M JUST WEARING THE SAME STUFF
FROM THE PLANE.
>> Jimmy: ARE YOU REALLY?
>> NO, I LOOK GREAT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I HAVE THAT ADAM LEVINE --
>> Jimmy: YOU HAVE THE SHIRT,
YEAH.
>> THEY KNOCK IT OFF THAT FAST.
>> Jimmy: IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
>> FROM THE MIXED REVIEW
COLLECTION AT KOHL'S.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Jimmy: YOU CAN KEEP THAT, BY
THE WAY.
YOU'RE WELCOME TO WEAR THAT
ANYWHERE.
>> A LITTLE BUMPER BIT.
I DID -- WAS SUPPOSED TO GO TO
THE SUPER BOWL.
>> Jimmy: SO YOU WEREN'T AT THE
GAME ITSELF?
>> I DID NOT.
I DID -- I GOT HIRED, THIS
ROBERT KRAFT GUY, GREAT GUY --
>> Jimmy: OWNER OF THE PATRIOTS.
>> HAD A BIG PARTY TONIGHT.
ACTUALLY SMALL, 250 PEOPLE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THE NIGHT BEFORE, FRIENDS AND
FAMILY, OWNERS, AND JEFF BEZOS,
BASICALLY ILLUMINATI, YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN.
>> Jimmy: UH-HUH.
PEOPLE ARE LAUGHING AS IF YOU'RE
KIDDING WHICH I KNOW YOU ARE
NOT.
>> THAT'S ALWAYS A GOOD CROWD.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THEY WERE GREAT.
AND JAMIE FOXX WAS THERE.
♪
AND HE WAS SORT OF THE BUP BUP
BUP BUP BUP, SHE'S A GOLD
DIGGER.
HE WAS DEEJAYING AFTER I WENT
OFF.
IT WAS FUN.
>> Jimmy: HOW DO YOU HANDLE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT, IN A ROOM
WITH 200 RICH PEOPLE WHO ARE
THERE FOR THE SUPER BOWL, AND
THEY'RE LIKE, WHAT IS HE DOING?
>> RIGHT, AND I WAS A SURPRISE
TOO.
IT'S ALWAYS WEIRD WHEN THEY'RE,
HUH?
[ LAUGHTER ]
I MET KRAFT WHEN HE GAVE US A
BOX, FOR GROWNUPS, A BOX AT THE
STADIUM FOR AC/DC, WAY BACK
THEN, ALL THE CAST.
I'VE ALWAYS SEEN HIM, HE WAS
ALWAYS NICE FOR ME.
HE GOT ME FOR THIS.
I GET NERVOUS.
PLUS HE HAD THESE BIG SCREENS.
EVERY TIME I LOOK OVER I SEE MY
SIDE PROFILE, WHICH IS
SICKENING.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I'M LIKE, WHO INVITED GOLLUM?
SO GROSS?
YOU LOOK FINE TO ME.
>> PEOPLE ARE WHISPERING.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I'M DOING MY JOKE.
I'M SORT OF MAKING FUN OF BRADY
AND GRONK.
DOING MY REGULAR CRUMMY ACT.
THEN I GO, HEY, IF YOU WIN, DO I
GET A RING?
I'M A SIZE 1, JUST KEEP IN MIND.
SO AFTER HE CAME RIGHT UP TO ME
WITH A RING RIGHT AFTER AND PUT
ON IT ME, ISN'T THAT FUNNY?
CAN YOU SEE THAT?
ISN'T THAT COOL?
>> Jimmy: IS THAT THE ONE THAT
WAS ON HIS FINGER?
>> YES.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> Jimmy: WOW, REALLY OUTDID
HIMSELF.
>> I THINK THAT'S HIM TRYING TO
GET IT BACK.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Jimmy: ALL RIGHT, PHOTO OP'S
OVER.
>> OH, THAT'S NOT IT YET.
THAT ONE WE -- SO I DO THE GIG.
I GET TICKETS IN HIS BOX FOR THE
SHOW.
>> Jimmy: NICE.
>> SO I GO AFTERWARDS --
>> Jimmy: FOR THE GAME?
>> FOR THE GAME WHICH WAS GREAT.
AFTERWARDS I GO TO THE PARTIES,
PUSHING THEM UP.
BY THE WAY, THE PARTIES ARE SORT
OF A DISASTER.
IT'S A LOT OF HYPE.
THERE'S BARRICADES, THERE'S
PROBABLY A HUNDRED PARTIES.
THE ONLY THING WORSE THAN
WAITING IN LINE IS ACTUALLY
GETTING IN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
SO CROWDED.
>> Jimmy: THAT'S 100% TRUE.
>> WHY DID I WANT THIS?
>> Jimmy: WHY AM I IN HERE?
>> CARDI B HAD ONE, ARE YOU
COMING TO MY PARTY?
WHEN ARE YOU GOING?
4:00 A.M.
I GO, 4:00 A.M.?
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT'S 9:15 NOW.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO HIT THE
POPUP INCUBATOR, COULD SOMEONE
TAP ON THE GLASS AROUND 3:30?
SO I BUZZ AROUND.
THEN THESE FOOTBALL PLAYERS
START GETTING IN MY HEAD.
OBVIOUSLY I'M DRUNK.
>> Jimmy: WHICH FOOTBALL
PLAYERS?
>> THERE WAS A LOT OF THEM.
TONY GONZALES.
HE GOT IN THE HALL OF FAME.
HE'S SORT OF A BUDDY.
THEN ALL THE -- THEY'RE ALL
THERE FOR HALL OF FAME AND THE
SHOW.
THEY'RE LIKE, YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO THE GAME TOMORROW?
I GO, YEAH!
THEY GO, WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
I GO, UH, WHAT?
THEY GO, EVERYONE LEAVES, ALL
THE COOL PEOPLE.
THEY LEAVE BEFORE THE GAME?
NO ONE UNDERSTANDS THIS THE.
I DIDN'T GET IT.
OF COURSE I WAS BUZZED AND THEY
WERE FAMOUS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
SO I CHANGED MY FLIGHT.
>> Jimmy: BECAUSE THEY TALKED
YOU OUT OF --
>> YEAH, THEY GO, IT'S THREE
HOURS, YOU HAVE TO LEAVE THREE
HOURS EARLY TO GET TO THE GAME,
A FIVE-HOUR GAME, TWO HOURS BACK
TO THE AIRPORT.
I GO, I'VE GOT STUPID KIMMEL
TOMORROW!
[ LAUGHTER ]
NO OFFENSE.
>> Jimmy: IT'S MY NICKNAME IN
HIGH SCHOOL.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> SO I GO, RRGH!
SO I GO, ALL RIGHT.
I BOOKED IT.
THEN I WOKE UP.
I GO, HUH?
I'M NOT STAYING?
SO I -- BUT IT FELT THAT IN THE
BOOTH, THE KRAFT BOOTH, WHICH
THEY'RE ALL COOL.
I DON'T KNOW ANYBODY THAT WELL.
THEN I WOULD FEEL KIND OF DUMB.
BECAUSE I'M FUN FOR A FEW
MINUTES.
BUT LET'S FACE IT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
FIVE HOURS OF ME GETS ANNOYING.
AND I KNOW I'D DO SOMETHING DUMB
LIKE BE OVER THE FOOD, GISELE,
DID YOU EAT THE LAST CHALUPE?
THESE ARE FOR EVERYBODY!
YOU POLISHED OFF THE THAT QUITOS
TO?
WHERE DO YOU PUT IT?
THEN KRAFT, THAT WAS FUNNY LAST
NIGHT.
TOUCHDOWN!
DID HE JUST SCORE?
DON'T LISTEN TO ME.
HE SAID, WHY ARE YOU TALKING,
SHOW'S OVER, DUDE.
NOTHING FROM ME ANYMORE.
I DON'T LIKE THE PLUS ONE LIFE.
>> Jimmy: YOU RELINQUISHED YOUR
TICKETS?
OR DID YOU GIVE THEM AWAY?
>> WELL ACTION PEOPLE ARE LIKE,
YOU CAN SCALP.
>> Jimmy: RIGHT, NO, YOU CAN'T.
>> ROBERT KRAFT WOULD LOVE TO
SIT NEXT TO TWO IDIOTS.
>> Jimmy: THEY'RE HERE,
ACTUALLY, YES.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THOSE GUYS, YEAH.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> Jimmy: THEY'RE FROM NORWOOD.
>> HUGGING GISELE ON EVERY FIELD
GOAL.
YEAH.
I KNEW I HAD TO GET OUT.
SO I GET OUT, BY THE WAY, IT'S
ALMOST OVER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I GET OUT.
AND THEY GO, WHAT'S SO HARD
ABOUT KIMMEL?
I GO, I'M BASICALLY GOING TO
COMPLAIN ABOUT JUST THIS.
I GO AND I GET ON MY FLIGHT AND
I GET ONE WITH A TV.
GUY, I'M JUST GOING TO WATCH THE
GAME AT EXACTLY THE SAME TIME.
I MEAN, NOT LIVE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO SEE, THE
SUPER BOWL?
I GO, YEAH.
OBVIOUSLY.
JAY GLAZER'S ON MY FLIGHT AND
SAM DARNOLD.
SHE GOES, WE'RE SHOWING
"BRIDESMAIDS."
I SAW IT!
AND EVERYONE ELSE!
SO WE WATCHED IT ON MY PHONE.
AND THEN WHEN MY PHONE STUCK,
WE'D GO TO HIS PHONE.
THEN SAM DARNOLD'S PHONE.
THEN HIS GOT STUCK, MINE'S ON
AGAIN.
HERE, SHOW A PICTURE.
>> Jimmy: THAT IS THE IDEAL WAY,
REALLY, TO WATCH THE SUPER BOWL.
>> I KNOW.
>> Jimmy: THERE YOU ARE.
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU HAD A BALL.
>> HE'S FROM THE JETS.
iPHONE NEGATIVE 3?
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHERE'S THE WINDEX?
YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
>> Jimmy: LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE
FINALLY SOLD YOUR SOUL TO THE
DEVIL IN THAT SHOT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
DAVID SPADE IS HERE WITH US,
WE'RE GOING TO GO TO COMMERCIAL,
BE RIGHT BACK.
>> Dicky: PORTIONS OF
“JIMMY KIMMEL LIVE” ARE BROUGHT
TO YOU BY NACHO FRIES.
NOW SERVING AT A TACO BELL NEAR
YOU.
Moderator:
This is the Chevy Equinox.
Various:
Beautiful. Wow.
Ooh, this is fancy.
Moderator:
That's the available
HD surround vision camera.
The top of your car?
Moderator:
Mm-hmm. It helps you see
dangers around the vehicle.
What is that?
Various:
Wait, wait, wait,
what is that? Oh, my...
(Mixed shouting)
Man:
These are big alligators.
Moderator:
So who's getting out first?
(Laughter)
Get 0% financing for 60 months
on most Equinox models.
Or, current GM owners
can get $3,500
total cash allowance
when financing
with GM Financial.
Find New Roads at your
local Chevy dealer.
when financing
with GM Financial.
♪
Celebrate Valentine's Day!
with hundreds of gifts
under $199!
And, find great deals on other
gifts she'll love!
Now through Valentine's Day.
Only at KAY.
How do we tell people they get
the best of both worlds
with Sprint?
How 'bout we get two-sport
legend, Bo Jackson...
S'up.
...holding a mermaid
...playing a keytar...
...and a bird-horse.
Woah.
Why don't you just tell people
Sprint can save them
more than $1,000
On an LTE Advanced Network
that's now up to 2x faster
than before.
Bo does know.
This is the best robot analogy
I've ever been in.
With a great network and savings
over Verizon and AT&T,
you get the best of both worlds
with Sprint.
Yee-haw!
When Girl Scout ingenuity
meets Dunkin' coffee,
you get a cup of can-do.
Girl Scout Cookie
inspired flavors
are back at Dunkin'.
Try Thin Mints, Coconut Caramel
or Trefoils shortbread flavors.
And get your $2 medium latte
or cappuccino from 2-6 PM.
America runs on Dunkin'.
You use the latest technology
to treat patients.
Grand Canyon University's online
programs in nursing make it
convenient for you to become the
expert every patient deserves.
Private. Christian. Affordable.
Nonprofit.
Visit gcu.edu/online
As a fitness junkie,
I customize everything -
bike, wheels, saddle.
Private. Christian. Affordable.
Nonprofit.
That's why I switched to
Liberty Mutual.
They customized my insurance, so
I only pay for what I need.
I insured my car,
and my bike.
My calves are custom too,
but I can't insure those...
which is a crying shame.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
When Girl Scout ingenuity
meets Dunkin' coffee,
you get a cup of can-do.
Girl Scout Cookie
inspired flavors
are back at Dunkin'.
Try Thin Mints, Coconut Caramel
or Trefoils shortbread flavors.
And get your $2 medium latte
or cappuccino from 2-6 PM.
America runs on Dunkin'.
[phone ringing]
Remember the way we
used to do things?
Hey man...
Like connect with friends?
Dig it!
Or get in shape?
Or sell a house
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
[crash]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
>> Jimmy: WE ARE BACK WITH DAVID
SPADE.
SONY MICHEL IS STILL TO COME.
MARGOT PRICE TOO.
YOU ARE A LOVER OF "THE
BACHELOR."
IS THAT FAIR TO SAY?
>> I DO WATCH, I DO INSTA
FEDERAL STORIES ABOUT IT.
I THINK IT'S HILARIOUS, YEAH.
>> Jimmy: YOUR INSTAGRAM STORIES
ARE THE BEST THING ABOUT "THE
BACHELOR."
>> THEY'RE R-RATED.
>> THEY'RE RAFT-RATED, I HIGHLY
RECOMMEND THEM.
I RARELY WILL SIT THROUGH
PEOPLE'S INSTAGRAM STORIES BUT I
WATCH YOURS.
>> I'M 100% BUZZED.
>> WHO DO YOU THINK IS GOING TO
WIN?
IS WIN EVEN THE RIGHT WORD TO
USE?
>> THERE ARE SO -- THEY'RE ALL
VERY CUTE.
IT'S ALWAYS SO CLOSE BECAUSE YOU
DON'T KNOW UNTIL YOU PEEL BACK
THE ONION AND START FIGURING
PEOPLE'S PERSONALITIES OUT.
THERE'S A COUPLE, NORTH
CAROLINA, THE GIRL KAITLIN, I
THOUGHT SHE WAS GOOD.
SHE'S GOOD.
WHATEVER.
>> Jimmy: SHE'S GOOD.
>> SHE HAS GOOD HAIR.
BUT THERE'S A LOT OF THEM THAT
ARE GREAT.
I THINK IF THEIR BACK STORIES
ARE FUNNY -- THE ONE GIRL WHOSE
MOM WAS IN JAIL OR SOMETHING,
SHE SHOULD ASK THEM NOT TO FILM
THE CALLING THE MOM IN JAIL.
I MEAN, THEN HE GAVE HER THE
ROSE AND I WAS LIKE, TAKE THIS
ROSE AS BAIL MONEY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THERE'S ALWAYS THINGS THAT YOU
CAN JOKE ABOUT.
SOMETIMES THEY DIRECT MESSAGE ME
AFTER I DO THE JOKES.
>> Jimmy: OH, THE ACTUAL --
>> YEAH, THE GIRLSS DO, OR THE
GUYS DO.
>> Jimmy: HAVE YOU EVER DATED A
BACHELOR CONTESTANT?
>> LET'S LOOK AT A CLIP.
NO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
NO, I HAVEN'T.
I KEEP IT STRICTLY FRIENDLY.
I DON'T WANT TO BE BIASED.
>> Jimmy: YOU'RE A PROFESSIONAL.
RIGHT, YOU CAN'T START DIPPING
INTO THAT POLL.
>> A JOKESTER, I CAN'T TAKE
SIDES.
>> Jimmy: YOU'RE GOING TO HAWAII
TO SHOOT A "HAPPY MADISON"
MOVIE.
>> YES, I AM.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> Jimmy: FOR NETFLIX.
>> THAT'S GOING TO BE FOR NET
FLEXION.
"FATHER OF THE YEAR" DID WELL SO
I GO OFF AND DO THAT.
I CAN'T WAIT.
IT'S GOING TO BE STOKED.
SANDLER'S NOT IN IT.
THIS IS ONE WHERE HE TAKES THE
TRAINING WHEELS OFF, PUSHES ME
OUT ON MY OWN.
>> Jimmy: THAT'S NICE OF HIM TO
SET YOU UP IN HAWAII.
>> I'VE NEVER REALLY SHOT A
MOVIE THAT WAS LIKE SUPER FUN
PLACE LIKE THAT.
I MEAN, BECAUSE I'M WORKING ALL
THE TIME BUT IT'S GREAT, SOUNDS
GOOD.
>> Jimmy: HOW IS YOUR HOUSE
DOING?
I KNOW YOU WERE NEAR THOSE
FIRES.
>> BIG FIRES.
YEAH, YOU KNOW, IT'S A MANSION.
YOU DIDN'T SAY THAT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Jimmy: HOW'S YOUR MANSION
HOLDING UP?
>> WHAT HAPPENED WAS, THE
FIRES -- THE SKY GOT SORT OF
DARK, A LITTLE SCARY.
IT WASN'T RIGHT ON TOP OF ME, A
COUPLE OF MILES AWAY FROM ALL OF
US.
I WAS WALKING AROUND ONE OF
THESE STREETS, THIS CAR BEEPS AT
ME.
I GO, HEY, MAN, I KEEP TALKING.
HONK, HONK.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M SUPPOSED
TO DO, RUN OVER?
HI!
THEN HE GOES, HEY, SNELLY.
I GO, UGH.
I WALK OVER.
IT WAS NELLY THE RAPPER.
HE GOES, SNELLY, IT'S NELLY.
OH, WHAT'S UP?
HE GOES, I GOT EVACUATED,
STAYING AT A HOTEL.
OH MY GOD.
ALL KIDDING ASIDE, WAS IT
GETTING HOT OUT THERE?
[ LAUGHTER ]
HE SAID, YEAH, IT WAS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
DID YOU HAVE TO TAKE OFF ALL
YOUR CLOTHES?
HE SAID, NO, I PUT THEM ON WHEN
IT EVACUATED.
WE DON'T JOKE AROUND, THESE ARE
SERIOUS THINGS.
>> Jimmy: NO, NO.
>> I SAID, WHAT ABOUT THE
VANITY?
IT MELTED OFF.
>> Jimmy: YOU COVERED ALL THE
BASES.
IT'S GREAT TO SEE YOU.
I'M GLAD EVERYTHING IS OKAY.
>> SEWNY MICHELE, IT'S COOL,
HE'S ON THE PAGES.
A GREAT SHOW TONIGHT.
>> Jimmy: YOU'RE WELCOME TO HANG
OUT.
DAVID SPADE, EVERYBODY.
"THE WRONG MISSY" WILL AIR LATER
THIS YEAR ON NETFLIX.
BE RIGHT BACK WITH SONY MICHEL!
?
-I know, it's not much,
but it's home.
Right, kids?
-Kids?
-Papa, Papa!
-[ Laughs ]
-You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
-Oh, yeah.
-This one is tiny like a child.
-Yeah, she is.
Oh, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most --
a home and auto bundle
from Progressive.
-Oh, sweetie,
please, play for us.
-Oh, no, I couldn't.
-Please.
-Okay.
[ Singing in Spanish ]
-Please.
-Okay.
Hey, Darryl.
Would you choose the network
rated #1 in the nation
by the experts,
or the one awarded
by the people?
Uh...
Correct! You don't
have to choose,
'cause, uh...
Oh!
(VO)
Switch to the network awarded
by the experts.
And get Apple Music included,
on us.
On both iOS and Android.
Why are we doing this?
Why are we doing what?
Using my Old Spice moisturize
with Shea Butter Body Wash...
All I wanted was to use your
body wash
And all I wanted was to have a
Body Wash.
THIS IS YOU SHOPPING.
AND THIS IS YOU
MAXIMIZING AT T.J.MAXX.
WHEN YOU GET MORE YOU FOR
YOUR MONEY, EVERY TIME,
IT'S NOT SHOPPING,
IT'S MAXIMIZING.
MAXX LIFE AT T.J.MAXX
"WOW"
"WHAT A NICE PLACE"
♪♪
I Hear it in the Background and
she's Watching too, saying
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
♪
[FRIEND]
I've never seen that before.
♪
I have...
Wow,
that's an aggressive yellow.
Pretty great, huh?
If you're a banana.
I find it very... appealing.
Kellogg's Raisin Bran
with Bananas.
Two scoops meet real
banana slices.
I've done a good job
of raisin ya.
Two scoops meet real
banana slices.
I call him "RoboChild."
Hey buddy! What do you wanna
be when you grow up?
I would like to be a
TurboTax Live CPA.
Don't you want to
be something else?
Yeah RoboChild, you
could be anything!
I want to help people get
their best possible refund.
Let's just break
it down, okay?
All TurboTax Live
CPAs
are human beings
with real emotions...
you're never going to be
emotionally complex enough
for that job.
I am sad. HAHAHAHA. HAHAHAHA.
Still perfecting emotion.
TurboTax Live now with
CPA's on Demand.
New Trident Spearmint Rush Vibes
start with a light crystal
coating,
then change into a smooth gum.
With bursts of spearmint flavor
that pop, pop, pop.
New Trident Vibes.
A Burst of Something New.
Sweat.
Dedication.
Cupcakes.
I'm Michael Griffin.
I'm Brian Orakpo.
We played football together for
the Titans.
Now, we own a cupcake shop.
We bake, we decorate.
I love this new Surface Pro.
It's light, it's sleek, it's
fast.
I'm able to draw what color
frosting we want.
We do a lot with social media.
We have funny videos that we do
in the bakery [laughs].
There's nothing that you can't
do on this device.
Cupcakes are a great business.
Oh yeah, as long as you don't
eat the profits!
>>> AFRICAN-AMERICAN
UNEMPLOYMENT, BEST NUMBERS
THEY'VE HAD, LITERALLY THE BEST
NUMBERS THEY'VE HAD IN HISTORY.
AND I THINK THEY LIKE ME A LOT.
AND I LIKE THEM A LOT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪ Ozempic®! ♪
Oh!
(announcer)
People with type 2 diabetes
are excited about
the potential
of once-weekly Ozempic®.
In a study with Ozempic®,
a majority of adults
lowered their blood sugar
and reached an A1C
of less than seven
and maintained it.
Oh!
Under seven?
And you may lose weight.
In the same
one-year study,
adults lost on average
up to 12 pounds.
Oh!
Up to 12 pounds?
A two-year study showed
that Ozempic® does not
increase the risk
of major cardiovascular events
like heart attack,
stroke, or death.
Oh!
No increased risk?
♪ Oh, oh, oh, Ozempic®! ♪
Ozempic® should not be the first
medicine for treating diabetes,
or for people with
type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not share needles or pens.
Don't reuse needles.
Do not take Ozempic® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine Neoplasia
Syndrome type 2,
or if you are
allergic to Ozempic®.
Stop taking Ozempic®
and get medical help right away
if you get a lump or swelling
in your neck,
severe stomach pain, itching,
rash, or trouble breathing.
Serious side effects
may happen,
including pancreatitis.
Tell your doctor if you have
diabetic retinopathy
or vision changes.
Taking Ozempic® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may increase the risk
for low blood sugar.
Common side effects are nausea,
vomiting, diarrhea,
stomach pain, and constipation.
Some side effects
can lead to dehydration,
which may worsen
kidney problems.
I discovered the potential
with Ozempic®.
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! Ozempic®! ♪♪
Ask your healthcare provider
if Ozempic® is right for you.
♪ If you love me, love me,
love me like you say ♪
♪ Darling, tell me
all the ways ♪
♪ Tell me all the ways ♪
♪ All the ways ♪
At the store, or to your door.
Target Run and Done.
♪
Celebrate Valentine's Day!
with hundreds of gifts
under $199!
And, find great deals on other
gifts she'll love!
Now through Valentine's Day.
Only at KAY.
Hey guys!
Check out our new trick.
♪♪
Steady.. - Roger!
Steady.. Now!
Go all in for what you love
with Tony and Kellogg's
Frosted Flakes.
Now in delicious NEW
Honey Nut.
As part of this complete
breakfast.
They're gr-r-r-reat!
I can't tell you who I
am or what I witnessed,
but I can tell you
Liberty Mutual customized
my car insurance so I
only pay for what I need.
Oh no, no, no,
no, no, no, no...
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
(Atlas)
Do humans like overpaying
with Verizon?
Don't they know they can get the
3rd, 4th and 5th lines
FREE with Sprint?
(Paul)
Yeah that means Sprint's
Unlimited Plan
gives you 5 lines for just
$20 per month, per line.
(Mom)
Really?
(Atlas)
Yes and you can save
more than $1,000
over Verizon and AT&T
with Sprint.
(Mom)
No way!
(Dad)
Robots don't lie.
(Atlas)
The man in the mom
jeans is correct.
(AVO)
Switch today and get 5 lines
for just $20 per
month per line.
See how you can save more than
For people with hearing loss,
$1,000 in the first year
with Sprint.
visit Sprintrelay.com
♪
It hasn't always
been easy, has it?
♪
There have been days
when you doubted yourself.
♪
And days when you
were ready to quit.
♪
But you didn't.
Because you had the courage to
venture into something powerful.
Education.
If I leave you with just
three words of advice:
never...stop...growing.
[cheering]
>> Jimmy: WELCOME BACK.
STILL TO COME, MUSIC FROM MARGOT
PRICE.
IN ADDITION TO RUSHING FOR
94 YARDS, OUR NEXT GUEST DID
SOMETHING VERY UNUSUAL LAST
NIGHT IN ATLANTA.
HE SCORED A TOUCHDOWN.
IT WOULD TURN OUT TO BE THE ONLY
TOUCHDOWN OF THE WHOLE GAME.
FROM THE SUPER BOWL CHAMPION
NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS, PLEASE
WELCOME, SONY MICHEL.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> Jimmy: YEAH LOOK AT THAT.
>> BE CAREFUL WILT IT NOW.
>> Jimmy: I'M BEING VERY
CAREFUL, DON'T WORRY, I WILL NOT
DESTROY THE LOMBARDI TROPHY.
WOULDN'T THAT BE SOMETHING THAT
I WAS THE ONE TO DESTROY IT
[ LAUGHTER ]
CONGRATULATIONS.
I HEARD YOU GOT A NEW GRILL TO
CELEBRATE THE OCCASION.
>> IT'S MY SUPER BOWL GRILL.
>> Jimmy: WHEN DID YOU GET IT?
>> TWO NIGHTS BEFORE THE SUPER
BOWL.
>> Jimmy: WHAT IF YOU HADN'T
WON?
WOULD THE GRILL HAVE GONE BACK?
WAS IT REFUNDABLE TYPE
SITUATION?
>> NAH.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I WAS GOING TO HAVE TO PUT IT IN
THE ARCHIVE FOR NEXT YEAR.
>> Jimmy: BOY, CONGRATULATIONS.
WHAT A GAME.
I MEAN, TO COME IN, IT'S YOUR
FIRST SEASON, AND HAVE THIS
HAPPEN.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
IT'S A DREAM.
IT'S LITERALLY A DREAM COME
TRUE, I WOULD THINK.
>> YES, IT IS.
WORDS CAN'T EXPLAIN THE EMOTIONS
THAT'S LIKE RUNNING THROUGH OUR
BODIES, MY BODY.
IT'S SO SURREAL.
>> Jimmy: WHAT DID YOU GUYS DO
LAST NIGHT?
WHAT WAS THE -- WHAT HAPPENED
AFTER THE TV CAMERAS LEFT?
>> AFTER THE TV CAMERAS LEFT --
EVERYBODY HEADED FOR THE PARTY.
>> Jimmy: FOR THE PARTY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHO PERFORMED AT THE BIG PARTY?
>> SNOOP DOGG.
MEEK MILL.
ONE OF MY FAVORITES.
LUDACRIS.
AND THEY HAD THAT THING ROCKING.
I WAS LIKE, MY PARENTS IN HERE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Jimmy: OH, YOUR PARENTS CAME?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> Jimmy: WAS THAT AT ALL
UNCOMFORTABLE?
>> NO.
>> Jimmy: DID THEY STAY TO THE
END, YOUR PARENTS?
>> NO.
>> Jimmy: GOOD.
>> MY MOM, SHE WAS THE PARTY
POOPER, SHE KIND OF GOT TIRED.
[ LAUGHTER ]
SO MY DAD HAD TO TAKE HER BACK
TO THE HOTEL.
SO MY DAD WANTED TO GET LIT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
IT WORKED OUT FOR BOTH OF THEM.
BEFORE YOU ASK, THIS IS MY FANNY
PACK.
THIS IS WHERE THE GRILL'S GOING
IN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
WELL PROTECTED.
>> Jimmy: ARE THERE MORE THAN --
DO YOU HAVE MORE THAN ONE GRILL
WITH YOU?
>> THEY COME OUT.
YOU NEVER SEEN GRILLES COME OUT.
ALMOST LIKE SOMEBODY TAKING OUT
THEY TEETH, UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> Jimmy: IT'S A REMOVABLE
GRILLE.
>> IT'S NOT PERMANENT.
>> Jimmy: WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
DO WITH IT?
PUT IT IN THERE?
OH, I SEE.
>> HOLD UP, WE'RE NOT JUST GOING
TO PUT IT IN THE BAG --
>> Jimmy: YOU'VE GOT A CASE FOR
IT.
[ LAUGHTER AND CHEERS ]
>> WE GOT A CASE FOR IT, WE GOT
A CASE FOR IT.
>> Jimmy: I HAVE A FEELING
YOU'RE GOING TO LEAVE THAT ON
THE PLANE OR SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT
LIKE THE PLAYERS' PARTY, LIKE
TOM BRADY, THIS IS THE SIXTH
TIME FOR HIM.
DID HE CUT LOOSE?
DID HE EAT A MELON SLICE OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
[ LAUGHTER ]
DID YOU SEE HIM REALLY ENJOYING
HIMSELF?
>> ACTUALLY, WHEN I GOT THERE, I
KIND OF EXPECTED IT TO BE LIKE
THE PLAYERS, THE PARENTS.
SO IT WAS MORE PEOPLE THAN I
THOUGHT.
>> Jimmy: I SEE.
>> SO HE KIND OF HAD HIS OWN VIP
AREA AT THE TOP.
>> Jimmy: I SEE.
>> SO I KIND OF FELT LIKE A FAN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
EVERYBODY WAS -- LIKE HAD THEIR
PHONES OUT.
I PULLED MY PHONE OUT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
EVEN THOUGH I JUST GOT OFF THE
FIELD WITH HIM.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
BUT I MEAN, HE WAS UP THERE WITH
HIS FAMILY, HE HAD HIS KIDS IN
THERE.
>> Jimmy: WHAT ABOUT THE BALL
ITSELF?
WHEN YOU SCORE THE TOUCHDOWN, DO
YOU GET TO KEEP THAT BALL?
HOW DO YOU PROTECT THE BALL?
>> YEAH, SO ONCE I SCORE, I HOLD
ON TO IT TIGHTLY.
BECAUSE SOMEBODY'S GOING TO TRY
TO GRAB IT.
>> Jimmy: RIGHT.
>> THEY GOING TO TRY TO KEEP IT.
SO I JUST TAKE IT TO THE
SIDELINE.
TRY TO DAP EVERYBODY UP WITH ONE
HAND.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I'MA GET HIT IN THE HEAD A
COUPLE TIMES.
USUALLY AFTER I TAKE OFF MY
HELMET, YOU KNOW, SO I DON'T GET
A CONCUSSION OR ANYTHING, WALK
OFF THE FIELD.
BUT MY EQUIPMENT MANAGER IS KIND
OF LIKE, IF HE SEES ME RUNNING
BACK TO THE SIDELINE WITH THE
BALL, BECAUSE USUALLY PEOPLE
CELEBRATE.
HE KNOWS I'M GOING TO KEEP THE
BALL.
AS SOON AS I LOOK AT HIM, HE'S
LIKE THIS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
SO I WAS LIKE, OH, HERE YOU GO.
>> Jimmy: YOU CAN TRUST HIM TO
HANG ON TO THAT THING FOR YOU.
>> USUALLY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
THIS IS SUPER BOWL.
SO NOW I'MA GO BACK TO MY
LOCKER, HOPEFULLY IT'S THERE.
>> Jimmy: WHAT ABOUT YOUR FAMILY
BACK HOME IN HAITI?
WAS THIS A BIG EVENT FOR THEM
WATCHING YOU IN THE SUPER BOWL?
DID THEY WATCH THE SUPER BOWL?
IS THAT INTERESTING TO PEOPLE IN
HAITI?
>> YOU KNOW, BEFORE, I DIDN'T
THINK THAT WAS A REALLY -- I
DIDN'T EXPAND MY MIND TO THINK
THAT PEOPLE OUT OF THE COUNTRY
IN HAITI WOULD BE WATCHING THIS
GAME.
AND BEFORE THE SUPER BOWL, I GOT
A INTERESTING VIDEO SENT TO ME
OF SOME KIDS WITH MY JERSEY AND
NUMBER ON.
>> Jimmy: WOW.
>> YOU KNOW, TELLING ME, GOOD
LUCK IN THE GAME.
THAT KIND OF WAS INSPIRING.
>> Jimmy: SURE.
>> I HAD TO STOP FOR A SECOND
AND THINK, MAN.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT I'M
DOING, IT'S BIGGER THAN MYSELF.
AND I GOT PEOPLE SUPPORTING ME
FROM ALL OVER THE PLACE.
IT WAS VERY ENCOURAGING.
>> Jimmy: I WOULD THINK SO,
YEAH.
I MEAN, THAT'S VERY EXCITING.
YOU WENT TO COLLEGE WITH TODD
GURLEY, WHO PLAYS FOR THE RAMS.
DID YOU GUYS INTERACT AFTER THE
GAME?
>> NO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
SOMEBODY TOLD ME HE WAS THE
FIRST ONE BACK IN THE LOCKER
ROOM.
>> Jimmy: OH, REALLY, WELL, HE'S
THE FASTEST GUY, THAT WOULD MAKE
SENSE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> MAKES SENSE, MAKES SENSE,
YEAH.
>> Jimmy: WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU SEEM LIKE A GREAT GUY.
AND I HOPE YOU ENJOY THIS.
YOU GOT THE PARADE TOMORROW
MORNING, RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> Jimmy: WOW, YOU'VE GOT TO GET
RIGHT OUT OF HERE AND GET OUT
THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
BE CAREFUL IN THAT PARADE, YOU
KNOW.
THIS IS WHERE, YOU KNOW, WHERE
YOU REALLY START TO GET TIRED,
YOU START TO LOSE YOUR MIND A
LITTLE.
THEN YOU'RE ON A TRUCK WITH ROB
GRONKOWSKI AND CRAZY THINGS
HAPPEN.
SO JUST BE CAREFUL ON THE PARADE
ROUTE.
REMEMBER THE KIDS IN HAITI.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I'M TRYING NOT TO FALL OFF
THE DUCK BOAT.
>> Jimmy: TRY NOT TO FALL OFF
THE DUCK BOAT, THAT'S KEY.
GRAT LATIONS.
SONY MICHEL, EVERYBODY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
HE'S THE SUPER BOWL CHAMPION.
BE RIGHT BACK WITH MARGOT PRICE!
>> Dicky: THE “JIMMY KIMMEL
LIVE” CONCERT SERIES IS
PRESENTED BY MERCEDES-BENZ.
THE BEST OR NOTHING.
>> Dicky: THE “JIMMY KIMMEL
LIVE” CONCERT SERIES IS
PRESENTED BY MERCEDES-BENZ.
THE BEST OR NOTHING.
>> Jimmy: I WANT TO THANK
DAVID SPADE AND SONY MICHEL,
APOLOGIES TO MATT DAMON.
“NIGHTLINE” IS NEXT, BUT FIRST,
THIS IS HER ALBUM “ALL AMERICAN
MADE.”
WITH "COCAINE COWBOYS," MARGOT
PRICE!
♪
♪ WELL THE BOYS ROUND
HERE AIN'T LIKE
THE BOYS BACK HOME ♪
♪ THEY DON'T PLANT
THE FIELDS THEY WON'T
WORK THE FARMS ♪
♪ THE BOYS ROUND HERE WELL
THEY TALK TOO FAST
WHEN THE TIMES GET HARD
NO THEY WON'T LAST ♪
♪ COCAINE COWBOYS
THEY'RE BAD IN THE SADDLE
BUT THEY'RE COMING FROM
NEW YORK LA AND SEATTLE ♪
♪ THEY'RE ALL HAT
THEY DON'T ROPE NO CATTLE
THEY DON'T RIDE NO BULLS ♪
♪ COCAINE COWBOYS
THEY NEVER GET SLEEP
WITH THEIR BLOODSHOT EYES
THEIR CIGARETTE TEETH ♪
♪ I WISH THAT
SOMEONE WARNED ME
STAY AWAY FROM THEM
COCAINE COWBOYS ♪
♪ OOOHH ♪
♪ WELL THEY'RE RIDING THE
RAILS RIGHT BEFORE THE SHOW
BETTER CALL UP JAMES
WHEN THE BAG GETS LOW ♪
♪ THE CROWD THINS OUT
THE LONGER THEY PLAY
YOU CAN'T WRITE A SONG
WITH NOTHING TO SAY ♪
♪ COCAINE COWBOYS
THEY'RE BAD IN THE SADDLE
BUT THEY'RE COMING FROM
NEW YORK LA AND SEATTLE ♪
♪ THEY'RE ALL HAT
THEY DON'T ROPE NO CATTLE
THEY DON'T RIDE NO BULLS ♪
♪ COCAINE COWBOYS THEY NEVER
GET SLEEP THEY'RE OUT IN
THE BARS AND THEY'RE GRINDING
THEIR TEETH ♪
♪ I WISH THAT
SOMEONE WARNED ME
STAY AWAY FROM THEM
COCAINE COWBOYS ♪
♪ I WISH THAT
SOMEONE WARNED ME
STAY AWAY FROM THEM
COCAINE COWBOYS ♪
♪ OOOHHH ♪
♪