Breathe In, You're Home.
This uplifting scent of
Tuscan fields can only be
the powerful clean of
Clorox Scentiva.
>> Judge Judy: You went there,
it was a terrible room, you got
out.
>> Announcer: A vacation
interrupted by a bad rental?
>> She was supposed to give us a
certain amount of money back.
She retained $891.50.
>> That is not true.
I did not retain --
>> Judge Judy: Don't talk --
Don't talk to anybody else.
>> Announcer: Interruptions are
a no-no.
>> I didn't understand when I
could interject.
>> Judge Judy: Never.
Do you take something that makes
you hyper?
>> I'm just naturally hyper.
I never drink caffeine, even.
[ Chuckles ]
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy."
You are about to enter
the courtroom of
Judge Judith Sheindlin.
Captions paid for by
CBS Television Distribution
>> Announcer: Craig Weinstein is
suing Ellen Schneiderman for the
return of money he paid for a
Beverly Hills vacation rental.
>> Byrd: Order! All rise!
This is case number 361 on the
calendar in the matter of
Weinstein vs. Schneiderman.
>> Judge Judy: Thank you.
>> Byrd: You're welcome, Judge.
Parties have been sworn in.
You may be seated.
>> Judge Judy: Mr. Weinstein,
you and your way were traveling
cross-country and saw an ad for
a cottage that you rented, based
upon the ad that you saw.
The cottage belongs to the
defendant.
>> That's correct, Your Honor.
>> Judge Judy: When you got
there, according to your
complaint, it was not what was
represented in the ad.
You had rented the cottage for
five nights?
>> Six nights, Your Honor.
>> Judge Judy: Six nights.
You and your wife stayed there
for one night.
>> That's correct.
>> Judge Judy: And then you
moved out and found other
accommodations -- I assume, at
greater expense.
>> That's correct.
We were scrambling.
>> Right.
>> Judge Judy: And you want a
refund of the five nights that
you did not spend there?
>> That's correct.
>> Judge Judy: That's what you
want?
>> It's actually more than
that, Your Honor.
>> Judge Judy: You want more
than that?
>> We want the entire six nights
refunded because
Miss Schneiderman breached our
settlement agreement.
She was supposed to give us a
certain amount of money back,
and she shorted us.
So since she breached the
settlement agreement, we're
looking for the entire six
nights.
>> Judge Judy: Okay, from here,
you're going to five nights if I
find that she misrepresented
the ad.
>> He already has received --
>> Judge Judy: Just a sec.
>> Oh, Okay.
>> Judge Judy: I'm not ready
for you.
>> Okay. Sorry.
>> Judge Judy: So, first, tell
me how much you paid for the
six nights.
>> We paid $2,244.
>> Judge Judy: $2,244.
>> That's correct.
>> Am I allowed to talk now? Oh.
>> Judge Judy: No, when I ask
you a question, you talk, unless
the figure he gave me is wrong.
>> Well, that includes a
refundable security deposit.
>> Judge Judy: Just a second.
All I asked, "Is that what he
paid you --$2,244?"
What she interjected is going to
affect my math, and math is not
my strong suit.
How much was the security
deposit?
>> $600, your honor.
>> Judge Judy: Did you get that
back?
>> Yes, I did.
>> Judge Judy: Fine.
4, 4, 6 -- $1,644.
So we are talking about $1,644.
That's gonna tell me how much it
was per night.
Or $274 per night.
>> It was actually not that,
because there was a $65 cleaning
fee and a $139 service fee.
It was $240 a night for the
room.
>> Judge Judy: Okay, how much
did you give him back?
>> Air-- or VRBO refunded him,
through me, $752.50.
>> Judge Judy: Okay.
>> Plus his --
>> Judge Judy: Plus a security
deposit.
>> Plus a security deposit.
And then I had to pay a fee
to the agency.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care.
I would actually --
>> That's correct.
>> All I retained, of all of
that, even though I couldn't
rebook the room at this point --
he was canceled --
>> Judge Judy: I don't care.
>> All I was able to retain was
$291.50.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care
about your fee.
>> Okay.
>> Judge Judy: Without the fees,
how much money did you retain?
>> I retained, it looks here --
this is the --
>> If I might, she retained
$891.50, which is what I paid
for one night's lodging.
>> That is not true.
I did not retain --
>> Judge Judy: Don't talk --
Don't talk to anybody else.
>> I did not retain that amount.
>> Judge Judy: Hey!
[ Raps desk ]
Stop.
>> Judge --
>> Judge Judy: Listen to me.
>> Oh, I'm sorry.
>> Judge Judy: If what you do is
interrupt, I'm just gonna give
him what he wants and throw
you out.
Do you understand?
>> Yes. I was confused when I
could talk.
>> Judge Judy: Chill.
>> $2,244 minus $1,352.50 is
$891.50.
That's what I paid.
>> Judge Judy: Just a second.
$892. And the room --
>> $891.50. Yeah, okay.
I'm sorry. [ Chuckles ]
>> Judge Judy: The room, per
night, was $240.
So $892 less --
>> Plus the cleaning fee.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care
about a cleaning fee.
I'm gonna look at the pictures
to see whether he's gonna get
this money.
>> Yes, but that was stated in
the contract.
>> Judge Judy: I'm talking.
>> Oh, sorry.
>> Judge Judy: 2, 5, which is
$652.
That's less one night's stay.
$652. Stayed there one night.
Now I'd like to see the
advertisement that you answered.
>> I have --
>> Judge Judy: Just show me the
advertisement that you answered.
>> Pretty nice house.
>> Judge Judy: It looks very --
It looks lovely.
>> $5.88 million.
>> Judge Judy: Shhhhhh.
>> Appraised value. I'm sorry.
>> Judge Judy: I understand that
you're upset, but you didn't go
there and have a heart attack
and end up in Cedars.
Nothing bad happened to you.
You went there, it was a
terrible room, you got out, you
went to Pacific Palisades, you
rented a nice room with your
wife, and you had another five
days there.
And it was lousy.
It's like going to a hotel in
the Bahamas or the Caribbean,
and all the plumbing it out for
the first night that you get
there.
"Oh, my God, it's terrible.
All the plumbing is out."
You can't use water, you can't
flush the toilets, or anything
else.
The next night, everything is
fixed, it's back on.
You stay.
They comp you for a night.
They comp you for two nights.
They do something.
They're sorry it happened.
"It was an accident.
We didn't mean for this pipe to
burst.
It wasn't..."
And then you had a nice time.
Nobody got an infection, nobody
ended up losing a limb.
So, Mr. Weinstein, get over it.
This is a very nice house.
>> I was with my wife, Judge.
>> Judge Judy: This is a very
nice -- So what?
>> And I have --
>> It was a six-night vacation.
We spent the whole second day
looking for alternate
accommodations.
>> I don't believe that, though,
'cause I got text that your wife
accidentally --
>> Judge Judy: Schneiderman?
>> Oh, I'm sorry.
>> Judge Judy: Shut up.
>> I'm sorry.
>> Judge Judy: You keep saying
you're sorry.
You can't control yourself?
Are you on some kind of
medication that you can't
control yourself?
No, I'm asking you a serious
question.
That's a serious question.
>> No.
>> Judge Judy: Then you keep
saying, "I'm sorry" and you keep
talking.
>> I didn't understand when I
could interject.
>> Judge Judy: When you could?
Never.
Not unless I ask you a question.
>> Okay, I misunderstood.
>> Judge Judy: You've never been
in a courtroom before?
>> No, I haven't.
>> Judge Judy: Never?
Is what you're telling me,
you've never been in a
courtroom?
>> Never been, other than a
traffic ticket.
>> She's a lawyer.
>> I'm not a lawyer.
I went to law school.
I'm not a lawyer.
[ Laughter ]
>> Judge Judy: Whatever you're
taking, you're not taking enough
of it.
>> You told me you were a
lawyer.
>> Judge Judy: Weinstein, I'm
gonna throw you out.
>> Sorry.
[ Spectators murmur ]
>> Judge Judy: I'm gonna throw
you out because -- bottom
line -- you're out $652.
My heart doesn't bleed for you.
Do you understand?
Okay, now I want to see pictures
of what your accommodation
looked like.
I see what the ad was.
>> I have pictures of the room.
>> Judge Judy: That's what I
want to see.
What you're telling me -- it was
one room?
>> Yes.
>> And the entire pool area.
And the entire pool area and all
the furniture out there.
>> Judge Judy: What kind of,
"Don't you interject unless I
ask you a question" don't you
understand?!
I'll tell you what I tell my
grandchildren -- "You don't live
in the lobby, you live in the
apartment."
[ Paper rustling ]
What did you put this up for?
What is this picture of?
Show her.
I'm gonna make a big circle
here.
What is this a picture of?
>> I can't see from here.
[ Pen scratches paper ]
I'm sorry.
Oh, those are comparable --
I don't know.
That's not my home.
[ Laughter ]
Oh, that was, I guess, when they
purchased the home.
That was, at one time, when it
was for sale, years ago, what it
looked like, but that's not what
my home looks like anymore.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care what
your home doesn't look like
anymore.
I want to know what it is that
he saw --
>> I never posted this.
This is from Zillow.
It was when the house was for
sale, before I ever purchased
it.
>> Judge Judy: Did you --
>> I never put that up.
>> Judge Judy: Do you have cop--
>> I have photos of the room.
>> Judge Judy: Shh. No, no, no.
>> I never posted that.
That's Zillow.
>> Judge Judy: I'm talking.
I want you to stop.
Do you take something that makes
you hyper?
>> I'm just naturally hyper.
I never drink caffeine, even.
[ Chuckles ]
>> Judge Judy: Do you have a
copy of the ad that was posted
for the property?
>> I do.
>> Judge Judy: I'd like to
see it.
>> Byrd: Ma'am.
>> Oh, I'm sorry.
>> Byrd: That's what I do.
[ Light laughter ]
>> See, I told you, I never
practiced law.
I just went to law school.
There's the listing, and here's
the photos with the listing.
[ Spectators murmur ]
>> Judge Judy: I want to see the
listing.
>> And the photos were part of
the listing.
>> Judge Judy: Shh.
Okay, great.
I want to see it.
[ Paper rustling ]
>> And there are photos of the
bedroom.
>> Judge Judy: Shhhhh!
Mr. Weinstein, I want you to
look at this, and I want you to
tell me whether this is what the
courtyard looks like in the
guesthouse.
>> That is an accurate picture
of the courtyard.
>> Judge Judy: And is this an
accurate picture of the pool
area?
>> Yes, it is, Judge.
>> Judge Judy: This is the
picture that you gave me.
Is that correct?
>> That's one of them, yes,
Judge.
>> Judge Judy: All right.
And this is a photograph of what
you gave me, Mr. Weinstein.
>> That is the bed, yes.
>> After he removed the --
>> Judge Judy: Shh!
>> Okay.
>> Judge Judy: Most annoying
person.
But this, Mr. Weinstein, is a
picture of the room, because
I've compared it to where the
nightstand is and compared it to
where the chest of drawers is.
This is a picture of the room.
>> May I see it?
>> Judge Judy: Absolutely.
>> And, Your Honor --
>> Judge Judy: Shh! I don't --
I didn't ask you anything!
>> That is her picture of the
room, yeah.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care.
That's a photograph.
That's not a painting.
>> That's correct.
>> Judge Judy: That's a
photograph of the room.
It doesn't look terrible to me.
Your picture looks terrible,
with your luggage and your
duffel bag.
>> It wasn't my duffel bag.
>> Judge Judy: Whosever --
>> It was on the floor when we
walked in.
>> Absolutely not true.
>> I don't travel with a
duffel bag.
>> Absolutely not true.
>> I came from New Jersey.
>> That's absolutely not true.
We would not leave a duffel bag.
>> Also, Judge, if I --
>> Judge Judy: They deserve --
They actually deserve each
other.
And do you know what happens to
people that deserve each other?
>> Byrd: I know, yeah.
>> Judge Judy: Last -- Last and
final warning.
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy"
continues in a moment.
>> Judge Judy: Listen to me very
carefully.
I would love to rule against you
because you are one of the most
annoying people that I've had to
deal with all day today.
[ Laughter ]
>> Announcer: And later today...
>> Judge Judy: Most 19-year-old
boys could live inside a closet
that contained nothing but dirty
socks.
[ Laughter ]
Very rarely do they care about
whether they have one or two
bathrooms.
They can actually go on a tree.
[ Laughter ]
♪
Introducing Fresh Step
Clean Paws,
with low-tracking
litter,
your vacuum becomes
a cat toy.
Let's make litter less
of a mess.
Let's start fresh.
>> Announcer: Closed captioning
is provided by...
For mild-to-moderate eczema,
there's EUCRISA.
It's steroid-free.
Do not use if you are allergic
to EUCRISA or its ingredients.
Allergic reactions may occur
at or near the application site.
The most common side effect
is application site pain.
Ask your doctor about EUCRISA.
>> Announcer: Real cases.
Real people.
"Judge Judy."
Craig Weinstein says
Ellen Schneiderman
misrepresented her Beverly Hills
vacation rental.
>> Judge Judy: Last and final
warning.
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: And then you're
gone, because I really don't
feel sorry for you.
I would feel sorry for you if I
actually thought you went into a
hovel.
You did not, and even if there
was a duffel bag here, it
wouldn't be so terrible.
This looks like a lovely room,
and it looks like a lovely
courtyard.
And it looks probably small for
200 bucks a night.
In Beverly Hills, that's what
you get.
You're also getting a pool.
I don't feel so sorry for you.
She gave you back money.
She gave you back a lot of
money.
I yelled at her. She's annoying.
Is this a picture of the
bathroom that you got to use?
>> There's two bathrooms. Oh.
I thought you were asking me.
I'm sorry.
>> Judge Judy: Is this a picture
of the bathroom that was in your
room?
>> Yes, the only bathroom.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care if
it's the only bathroom.
She said it was the only
bathroom in the ad.
>> [ Gasps ]
>> Shut up.
>> Judge Judy: The ad says that
there is one bathroom.
The ad says that you could use
another bathroom outside, that's
in the pool area.
Put your hand down.
That you can use another
bathroom, that the person who
lives in the main house will not
use it during the course of your
stay.
That's what it says in the ad.
I read it.
It never said that you had a
room with two bathrooms.
>> No.
>> Judge Judy: Okay, and this
was your bathroom?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Is that right?
Is that right?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: You don't get any
money back.
It's very nice that you gave him
that much back.
>> Judge, the picture of the
closet that she gave you had a
refrigerator in it.
The picture of the drawers had
pillows and blankets in it.
My wife couldn't get out of the
bed on her side.
>> That's not --
>> She had to come over to my
side.
The picture that you showed me
that Ellen provided, the door
was open.
>> That is absolutely --
>> So it appears to be bigger.
Anyone could take a picture.
If you look at the --
>> I have 80 five-star reviews.
>> Judge Judy: Just a sec.
Listen to me very carefully.
I would love to rule against you
because you are one of the most
annoying people that I've had to
deal with all day today.
I find it difficult because the
200 bucks in Beverly Hills, I
think he got a reasonable
accommodation.
If he didn't like it, he was
returned most of his money.
You didn't have enough time to
re-rent it for the next six
nights.
And not awarding any money,
Mr. Weinstein.
>> But we had an agreement.
>> Judge Judy: We are done.
We are finished.
>> I know, but we had an
agreement, Judge.
She didn't give me all my money
back.
>> Judge Judy: That's why you
came.
>> Byrd: Parties are excused.
>> But why did we have an
agreement?
>> Byrd: Parties are excused.
>> The room was a converted
pantry.
>> He absolutely lied about
that.
>> My wife said, "I can't even
stay here one night."
>> But he also wanted the
difference of some hotel he said
he stayed in, and yet provided
no proof whatsoever of that
hotel.
>> Ironically, she's no longer
on the website, because I think
she's come to her senses.
>> I never really did it for the
money.
>> You can't rent out a pantry
closet.
>> I was nice to give him four
of his six nights back.
>> Announcer: And now the next
case.
>> Byrd: All parties in the
matter of (plaintiff) vs.
(defendant),
step forward.
>> Announcer: 22-year-old
Meghan Tauzier and her mother,
Candy Tauzier, are suing
Meghan's ex-boyfriend,
21-year-old Gage Minick,
for a security deposit, the
return of horse-riding jeans,
and unpaid rent.
>> Judge Judy: Miss Tauzier,
you're 20 years old.
You met him on some sort of a
dating app.
He's 19 years old when you met.
You knew each other for a few
months.
I assume you were living at your
mother's house, and you were
living at your mother's house.
>> Yes, Your Honor.
>> Judge Judy: That's where
19-year-old boys usually live.
And you decided, when you were
20 and he was 19, that you would
move out of your parents' house
and go and live together.
And he was 19, and he was gonna
get a job.
And you were 20 and, according
to you, said, "I decided to go
to school for a time, and he was
gonna get a job at 19."
They can't find their way out of
a front door when they're 19.
They don't know how to do the
laundry when they're 19.
They don't know how to care for
themselves when they're 19.
So, you lived in one apartment
first and didn't have the
security deposit, so you put
down the security deposit, $500,
which is part of what you want
back, because he was supposed to
take care of everything.
He was supposed to take care
of you while you went to school.
Is that what you wrote?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: [ Laughs ]
[ Laughter ]
It's a joke.
And then, according to what you
wrote, the apartment -- he
didn't like the apartment.
He didn't think it was good
enough for the two of you.
>> That's incorrect.
>> Judge Judy: Listen, most
19-year-old boys could live
inside a closet that contained
nothing but dirty socks.
[ Laughter ]
Very rarely do they care about
whether they have one or two
bathrooms.
They can actually go on a tree.
[ Laughter ]
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy"
continues in a moment.
>> Judge Judy: Did anybody pay
the $1,990?
>> I did, Your Honor.
>> Judge Judy: Did you?
>> I did.
>> Judge Judy: Did you pay
anything?
>> No, I didn't.
>> Judge Judy: [ Laughs ]
>> I had taken myself off the
lease.
We both signed a paper that took
my name off the lease and made
me not liable for anything.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care!
[ Laughter ]
I'm mildly obsessed
with numbers.
So, I started with
the stats regarding my
moderate to severe
plaque psoriasis.
Like how HUMIRA
has been prescribed
to over 300,000 patients.
And how many patients saw
clear or almost clear skin
in just 4 months -
the kind of clearance
that can last.
HUMIRA targets and
blocks a specific source of
inflammation that
contributes to symptoms.
Numbers are great.
And seeing clearer skin
is pretty awesome, too.
That's what I call
a Body of Proof.
HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections, including
tuberculosis, and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened, as
have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor if you've
been to areas where certain
fungal infections are
common and if you've had
TB, hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Want more proof?
Ask your dermatologist
about HUMIRA.
This is my Body of Proof.
What's better than having fast,
reliable WiFi with
coverage throughout your home?
How about having Internet
that can help you save
on wireless phone service?
Xfinity gives you
the fastest speeds
from America's best
Internet provider
to stream on
all your devices.
Plus, with Xfinity
Mobile included,
you can switch
your wireless carrier
and save hundreds
of dollars a year.
Now that's
simple, easy, awesome.
Get started for $39.99
a month for 12 months.
Plus, ask how you can
get Xfinity Mobile included
so all you pay for
is data. Switch today.
>> Announcer: Real cases.
Real people.
"Judge Judy."
Meghan Tauzier says ex-boyfriend
Gage Minick owes for her share
of the security deposit, the
return of her jeans, and rent.
Gage is countersuing for
Meghan's share of an
early-lease-termination fee.
>> Judge Judy: Now, what you
wrote here was that he wanted a
nicer apartment.
>> That's actually incorrect.
She wanted a nicer apartment.
She didn't like the old one.
>> Judge Judy: Usually, it's
girls that don't like the
apartment.
Anyway, you moved into another
You weren't working.
apartment.
He couldn't maintain the other
You weren't working.
apartment, 'cause it was more
He couldn't maintain the other
expensive than the first.
apartment, 'cause it was more
>> It was cheaper.
expensive than the first.
It was cheaper than the first
>> It was cheaper.
apartment.
It was cheaper than the first
>> Judge Judy: Cheaper.
apartment.
Couldn't maintain it, and you
>> Judge Judy: Cheaper.
weren't working.
Couldn't maintain it, and you
>> Yes, I was a full-time
weren't working.
student, not working.
>> Yes, I was a full-time
>> Judge Judy: You weren't
student, not working.
working, and so you were living
>> Judge Judy: You weren't
there and he was paying the
working, and so you were living
expenses.
there and he was paying the
>> Yes.
expenses.
>> Judge Judy: [ Laughs ]
>> Yes.
[ Laughter ]
>> Judge Judy: [ Laughs ]
And then [Chuckles] you did what
[ Laughter ]
most moronic teenagers do, when
And then [Chuckles] you did what
they try this thing, it doesn't
most moronic teenagers do, when
work out, you broke the lease
they try this thing, it doesn't
and then went and moved in
work out, you broke the lease
with you.
and then went and moved in
And you are here as a
with you.
co-plaintiff 'cause you want him
And you are here as a
to pay rent.
co-plaintiff 'cause you want him
>> Yes.
to pay rent.
>> Judge Judy: [ Laughs ]
>> Yes.
[ Laughter ]
>> Judge Judy: [ Laughs ]
Were they sleeping in the same
[ Laughter ]
room?
Were they sleeping in the same
>> Yes.
room?
>> Judge Judy: Was it her room?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Had it been her
room when she was 19?
>> Well, we had just moved in.
We hadn't been living there.
>> It was a guest room.
>> So it was a guest room.
>> Judge Judy: Oh.
>> It was not my bed, my
furniture.
None of it was mine.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care.
It's irrelevant.
If your daughter came home,
where would she have slept?
>> In the guest room.
>> Judge Judy: Okay, that's
where she slept with her
boyfriend?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: With your
permission?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Perfect.
What article of clothing do you
claim that he has that belongs
to you?
>> He has a pair of jeans.
>> Judge Judy: Pair of jeans.
Do you have her jeans?
>> No, I don't, Your Honor.
>> I have a text that says he
does have them.
>> Judge Judy: You're not
cuddling with her jeans at
night, are you...
>> No, Your Honor.
[ Laughter ]
>> Judge Judy: ...Mr. Minick?
[ Chuckles ]
Do you know where they are?
>> No, ma'am, I don't.
>> Judge Judy: He doesn't know
where they are.
Now, let's get to the broken
lease first.
Broken lease costs, according to
you, $1,990.
>> That's correct.
>> Judge Judy: That's for the
second apartment, to break the
lease.
In whose name was the lease?
>> Both of ours.
>> Judge Judy: Did anybody pay
the $1,990?
>> I did, Your Honor.
>> Judge Judy: Did you?
>> I did.
>> Judge Judy: Did you pay
anything?
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy"
continues in a moment.
Closed captioning
sponsored by...
My cholesterol is borderline.
I can worry about it, or do
something about it.
Garlique helps maintain healthy
cholesterol naturally,
and it's odor-free, and
pharmacist recommended.
Garlique
>> Announcer: Real cases.
Real people.
"Judge Judy."
Live from the Starlite Lounge.
♪ One plus one equals
too little too late ♪
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
>> Judge Judy: Did anybody pay
the $1,990?
>> I did, Your Honor.
>> Judge Judy: Did you?
>> I did.
>> Judge Judy: Did you pay
anything?
>> No, I didn't.
>> Judge Judy: [ Laughs ]
[ Laughter ]
>> I had taken myself off the
lease.
We both signed a paper that took
my name off the lease and made
me not liable for anything, and
I have that copy here.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care!
[ Laughter ]
You lived there with him.
You went from that apartment to
your mom's house, so you lived
in that house.
You slept with him in that
house, cuddled with your
boyfriend in that house.
What difference did it make if
you took your name off the
lease?
He paid $2,000 to get you out of
the lease because you weren't
working and he was working, and
you couldn't afford the
apartment.
You're supposed to be an
independent woman, on your own,
so you can take care of yourself
and not rely on somebody else to
take care of you when you're 20.
And if you don't, you stay home
in your mother's house.
He's not gonna pay you any
money.
If you put in a security deposit
of $500, I'll force you to pay
half of what he paid, if he can
show me he paid 2 grand to break
the lease.
Do you understand?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Grow up!
Your case is dismissed.
We're done.
>> What about my counterclaim?
My counterclaim, Your Honor?
>> Byrd: Parties are excused.
You may step out.
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy"
continues in a moment.
And on the next "Judge Judy"...
>> I'm happy with the decision.
Don't really have too many
complaints.
>> Well, she's my daughter.
>> I paid my half, she paid her
half at the beginning.
>> Well, the couldn't afford it.
>> They had me doing a lot of
stuff for them, kind of treated
me like a slave.
>> We always got along.
>> If there was a TV remote on
the table, they'd be like, "I'm
right here, but can you reach it
for me?"
>> If the whole thing happened
over, I wouldn't have let him
move in.
>> Definitely gonna wait it out.
Not gonna do it immediately.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
>> Judge Judy: May I see the
scratches on your car?
>> Announcer: Vandalism gets a
spell check.
>> Judge Judy: You go to
college?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: You should study