>> Announcer: She already pays
him alimony.
>> Judge Judy: $1,400 a month
for 8 1/2 years.
>> Announcer: But he expects
more.
>> Judge Judy: There were some
bills that you paid in error.
>> Cellphone bills.
>> I don't think --
>> Judge Judy: I don't care what
you think.
>> Announcer: Is it her mistake,
her problem?
>> Judge Judy: How would you
like it if the bank told you to
suck it up?
>> Uh...
>> Judge Judy: Well, that's the
way she feels about paying your
phone bill.
She's already got to suck up
paying you alimony.
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy."
You are about to enter
the courtroom of
Judge Judith Sheindlin.
Captions paid for by
CBS Television Distribution
Jennifer Doane is suing her
ex-husband, John Doane, for the
return of alimony she overpaid.
>> Byrd: Order! All rise!
Your Honor, this is case number
402 in the calendar in the
matter of Doane vs. Doane.
>> Judge Judy: Thank you.
>> Byrd: You're welcome, Judge.
Parties have been sworn in.
You may be seated.
>> Judge Judy: Ms. Doan, you and
the defendant were married,
according to what I read, for
approximately nine years.
And you do not have children
together.
Each of you has children from
previous marriages or
relationships, and I believe
that those children lived with
you while you were married.
So far correct?
>> That is correct.
>> Judge Judy: And that marriage
terminated in what month and the
year so that I have that?
>> It's January of 2017.
>> Judge Judy: And pursuant to
the terms of that decree,
Mr. Doan's children remain with
him.
You have two children?
>> I have one.
>> Judge Judy: You have one.
So your one child remained with
you, and your two children are
with you.
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Now, who stayed
in the marital home?
>> We sold it.
>> Judge Judy: And pursuant to
the terms of that agreement,
you, Mrs. Doane, as the
breadwinner in the family, at
least for a good part of those
nine years, were required to pay
Mr. Doane six years of alimony.
>> Eight years.
>> Judge Judy: Eight years?
>> Eight and a half years, yes.
>> Judge Judy: In what amount?
>> $1,400 a month.
>> Judge Judy: It is your claim
in this case that, in addition
to paying him, which you are
paying him the $1,400 a month,
and that is current -- is that
correct, Mr. Doane?
>> Yes.
Well, she missed a couple
months.
>> But I paid it back.
>> Yeah.
>> Judge Judy: There were some
bills that you paid in error.
>> Correct.
>> Judge Judy: That's what
you're alleging.
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: What bills were
those?
>> That was our AT&T cellphone
bills.
>> Yours, joint bill?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: When did you pay
that bill?
>> From when the divorce was
filed against me, where I had
temporary alimony, until I
stopped paying it September of
2018.
>> Judge Judy: Well, I'm just
interested right now in anything
subsequent to the divorce.
>> Right.
And that should've been --
>> Judge Judy: I'm not talking
about filing.
I'm talking about subsequent to
the divorce when the court fixed
everyone's responsibility, and
that was $1,400 a month for
8 1/2 years, custody -- they
made those arrangements,
directed the sale of the house.
So, what bills and in what
amount did you pay subsequent to
the divorce that were not
required by the divorce?
>> I paid everything from
1/5/2017 until July of 2018.
>> Judge Judy: And so that we
don't have to go through all of
this, perhaps we can come to an
agreement with regard to,
because I'm sure you've
discussed this.
>> A lot.
>> Judge Judy: How much is the
amount of those bills that you
were not required to pay that
you did pay?
>> The amount I have those back
to when I originally started
paying the cellphone bill for
both of us --
>> Judge Judy: No, no, no.
>> Yeah, I don't have the total
amount.
>> Judge Judy: Well, then let's
get that amount.
Anything after the divorce that
you were not required to pay but
paid in error is what your
allegation is.
>> Right.
>> Judge Judy: You understand
that, sir?
>> Yes. Yes, I do.
>> Judge Judy: Do you have the
figure?
>> I think it's $1,165.
>> I'm calculating it right now,
Your Honor, based on after the
divorce was final.
So, it's $2,987.
>> Judge Judy: Okay, I'm going
to ask the two of you to go
outside and take a look at those
bills.
This is not a determination of
whether or not he's responsible
to repay you.
This is just so that you can
come up with a figure to give
me.
Do you understand?
>> Understood.
>> Judge Judy: I'll see you back
here in five.
>> Okay.
>> Byrd: Parties are excused.
This case will be recalled.
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy"
continues in a moment.
>> Judge Judy: Don't tell me
what your lawyer tells you!
That's why I'm a judge and I'm
here and I'm uber-successful.
I guarantee you much more
successful than your lawyer.
Guaranteed.
>> You're a wonderful, famous
person.
>> Judge Judy: Bingo, because
I'm smart.
>> Announcer: And later today...
>> Judge Judy: When you got
incarcerated for what?
>> I act stupidity and went out
there and put two tires on flat.
>> Judge Judy: Oh, so you lost
your temper.
>> Yeah.
>> Judge Judy: And you flattened
her tires in front of the
police.
Br
25% of your mouth.
LISTERINE® cleans
virtually 100%.
Helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%.
Always go for 100.
Bring Out the Bold™
>> Announcer: Closed captioning
is provided by...
For mild-to-moderate eczema,
there's EUCRISA.
It's steroid-free.
Do not use if you are allergic
to EUCRISA or its ingredients.
Allergic reactions may occur
at or near the application site.
The most common side effect
is application site pain.
Ask your doctor about EUCRISA.
>> Announcer: Real cases.
Real people.
"Judge Judy."
In a case recalled from earlier
today, Jennifer Doane says
ex-husband John Doane owes for
the return of alimony she claims
she overpaid.
>> Judge Judy: Okay, did we
agree on a figure?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Good.
Thank you.
>> Byrd: Okay.
>> It's $3,337.03.
And that's from 1/5/17, when the
divorce was final, to July 13,
2018.
>> Judge Judy: When you stopped
paying those bills?
>> Correct.
>> Judge Judy: So, you indicated
one was a phone bill.
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: What other bills?
>> That's it.
>> Judge Judy: Just phone?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: And whose phone
bill was it after the divorce?
>> It was in his name.
But I was paying it -- automatic
payments.
>> Judge Judy: Okay.
Ball's in your court.
>> I don't think --
>> Judge Judy: I don't care what
you think.
>> Okay.
>> Judge Judy: What you think is
irrelevant.
All I want to know is --
>> I believe what the paper
says, and the paper from my
attorneys, and they had said I
have no obligation to pay her.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care what
they said.
>> Okay, well, it's on here.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care what
they said.
I don't care what you think.
>> Okay.
>> Judge Judy: Do you pay your
bills now?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Other than
receiving the $1,400 a month
from the plaintiff, do you have
any other source of income?
>> Yes.
I get $1,600 from disability.
>> Judge Judy: So, let's say
instead of sending you $1,600
for disability, the government
sends you $3,600 for three
months, and then they said to
you, "We made a mistake.
You owe us $6,000."
Would you say to the government,
"That was your mistake"?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: "It had nothing
to do with me.
That was your mistake."
You suck it up.
I'm gonna give you another
example.
>> Okay.
>> Judge Judy: Let's say you
take your $1,600 a month
disability and your $1,400 a
month in alimony, and you put it
in your checking account and
your checking account credits
you with $16,000 and $14,000.
And you say, "Ooh.
Windfall for me.
I'm going out to buy myself a
brand-new computer."
And then the bank says to you,
"Listen, we're reversing all
those things, and you owe us
$20,000."
You think you would tell the
bank to suck it up?
>> I might do that.
>> Judge Judy: You might?
>> Yeah, because --
>> Judge Judy: Let me tell you.
Let me tell you why you would
not be successful.
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Legally why you
would not be successful.
Now, let's say instead of the
bank giving you $20,000 extra,
instead of depositing your check
as $1,600 and $1,400, they
deposited it as $600 and $400.
You didn't notice it for a
couple of months.
All of a sudden you say, "My
bank account is shy $2,000."
You look at it.
You say, "They didn't credit me
with the 1.
They missed the 1.
You know, they thought it was
part of the dollar sign.
They missed the 1, and they owe
me $2,000."
How would you like it if the
bank told you to suck it up?
>> Uh...
[ Laughter ]
You mean it only works when it's
in your favor?
>> No.
>> Judge Judy: I want you to
answer my question.
You said you would tell the bank
to suck it up.
>> No, I would not say that.
>> Judge Judy: You probably
couldn't tell the federal
government to suck it up 'cause
they'd suck you up.
But if it worked not in your
favor and they took your money,
you would say, "I deserve my
money.
You stole my $2,000."
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: "Because I put in
$1,600 and you only gave me
credit for $600.
I put in $1,400.
You only gave me credit for
$400.
You stole $2,000 from me."
Wouldn't you feel that way?
I would feel that way.
>> This is --
>> Judge Judy: Don't tell me
what your lawyer tells you!
That's why I'm a judge and I'm
here and I'm uber-successful.
I guarantee you much more
successful than your lawyer.
Guaranteed.
>> You're a wonderful, famous
person.
>> Judge Judy: Bingo, because
I'm smart.
Because I just gave you two
examples, and I'm asking you
would you think that the bank
stole $2,000 from you that you
should have in your pocket?
>> Yep.
>> Judge Judy: Yes.
Well, that's the way she feels
about paying your phone bill.
She's already got to suck up
paying you alimony when you have
no children together and you had
a relatively short-term
marriage.
She already has to suck that up.
She did it, and she's paying
you.
She doesn't have to overpay you.
Judgment for the plaintiff in
the amount of $3,337.
We're done.
>> Thank you.
>> Byrd: Parties are excused.
You may step out.
>> I am very happy with the
decision, obviously.
>> I raised her kids.
I did a lot of stuff.
>> Well, this is probably the
same reason that we're not
married any longer --
communication problems.
>> Money hungry.
Like, if I found a dollar bill
on the floor...
>> No, I don't think he was
stealing.
I think he just needed to pay me
back, and he wasn't making it
happen.
>> ...she would make me give her
99 cents of it.
>> I just want to pay the
alimony, the extraordinarily
high alimony.
>> I am totally for that.
>> I just want to pay it until
it's done and that's it.
>> Living and being nice to
Jennifer.
I love her still.
>> I know that he does, and
that's 'cause I'm a great woman.
>> Announcer: And now the next
case.
>> Byrd: All parties in the
matter of Hall vs. Grable, step
forward.
>> Announcer: Dwayne Hall is
suing his ex-girlfriend,
24-year-old Angela Grable, for
the value of an S.U.V. she stole
from him.
>> Judge Judy: Mr. Hall, how
long were you and the defendant
living together?
>> About seven or eight months.
>> Judge Judy: What kind of car
do you drive?
>> A Regal, 2011 Regal, and I
drive my Infiniti FX35.
>> Judge Judy: You drive a 2011
Regal?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: And that's what
you were driving when you met?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: You were driving
the 2011 Regal?
>> Yes, and the Infiniti.
I have both cars.
>> Judge Judy: Just --
[ Laughter ]
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy"
continues in a moment.
>> Judge Judy: Who is this?
>> This is my wife.
>> Judge Judy: What'd you bring
her for and why didn't you bring
Kenny?
>> I brought her based on the
fact that she been texting --
>> Judge Judy: I just find it
hard to believe that Kenny paid
to get it out and just
serendipitously you retitled the
car half in her name, half in
yours.
♪
They're all going in the same
direction
but in very different ways
and Pampers gives all of them
our driest best fitting diaper.
Pampers Cruisers with three-way
fit.
They adapt at the waist, legs
and bottom
with up to twelve hours of
protection
for all the freedom to move
their way.
In Pampers Cruisers
Only Pampers Diapers
are the number one choice of
hospitals,
nurses and parents.
>> Announcer: Real cases.
Real people.
"Judge Judy."
Dwayne Hall says ex-girlfriend
Angela Grable stole his S.U.V.
Angela is countersuing for
utility bills, car repairs, and
pain and suffering.
>> Judge Judy: Now, the 2005
Infiniti was in the shop.
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: In what month and
year did you take it there?
>> I took it there February 27th
of 2018.
>> Judge Judy: And in what month
did you meet the defendant?
>> In April.
>> Judge Judy: So the car had
already been in the shop for
several months?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: What was wrong
with the car?
>> Well, I had let a friend use
the car, and he messed the
brain.
The brain or something went out
on the car.
>> Judge Judy: The car was a
mess because you had lent it to
somebody.
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Did you get a
price for fixing it?
>> Yes.
I have the price for fixing it,
and my friend that I had let use
it, he's the one that took fault
for it, and he paid for it.
>> Judge Judy: I don't believe
that.
>> I have the receipts right
here.
>> Judge Judy: Is he here?
>> No, but I have the receipts.
>> Judge Judy: Okay.
You say you paid for it.
>> Yes, ma'am, I did.
>> Judge Judy: Do you have proof
of that?
>> I do not have the actual
receipt from the shop, but I do
have -- I basically get
financial aid, and the whole
reason the car even got put in
my name was upon the agreement
that I paid to get it out of the
shop.
>> Judge Judy: That's what you
say.
And is what you're telling me
was paid for by financial aid?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: And in what month
was the car taken out of the
shop, Mr. Hall?
>> August 27th of 2018.
>> Judge Judy: And what's the
name of your friend who paid for
the car?
>> It's Kenny.
>> Judge Judy: Kenny what?
>> I got his name -- I don't
know his last name by heart.
>> Judge Judy: Who is this?
>> This is my wife.
>> Judge Judy: She didn't pay
for the car to come out of the
shop.
>> No, she didn't pay for the
car to come out the shop.
>> Judge Judy: And she doesn't
know that the car was in the
shop, how much it cost, who got
it out.
>> Well...
>> Judge Judy: She wasn't there.
>> She was there when I put the
car in the shop.
>> Judge Judy: Not in. Out.
>> No, she was not there.
>> Judge Judy: But Kenny was.
>> Kenny was there.
>> Judge Judy: And Kenny was the
one that you said paid for it.
>> Kenny was the one that paid
for it, signed it out.
>> Judge Judy: Then what'd you
bring her for and why didn't you
bring Kenny?
>> I asked him could I bring
Kenny, but it was too late
because he works and stuff like
that.
So I brought her based on the
fact that testimonies that she
been texting --
>> Judge Judy: Oh, I don't care
about texting.
I don't care about the two of
them.
I don't care about anything.
I just find it hard to believe
that Kenny paid to get it out
and just serendipitously you
retitled the car half in her
name, half in yours.
Now, I'd like to hear a good
story, sir, about the car came
out in August of 2018, and in
what month was it titled in
Ms. Grable's name and yours?
>> The month that it was titled
in her name was September.
>> Judge Judy: And in September,
you were still married.
>> Yes, I was still married.
>> Judge Judy: I'm gonna ask you
all these questions because,
bottom line, you say it's your
car.
She says it's her car.
That's the issue.
The title to the car was in both
of your names.
Now, would you tell me a good
reason that I'm gonna believe
why, after your car has been in
the shop February, March, April,
May, June, July, and August, the
car comes out in August, and
then it's retitled in not only
your name but your name and the
defendant's name.
I want you to give me a good
story about that.
>> Okay.
I had put the car in her name
because --
>> Judge Judy: Because.
>> Because when I got it out the
shop, my license was suspended.
I have a D.U.I. on my record, so
I was like, "If the car's gonna
be used, you driving me around,
and you're going back for
school," so I said, "Based on
the fact of that, I don't want
to have the car solely in my
name so they'll be harassing
you," so I put her name on it.
>> Judge Judy: What about your
other car?
Did you put your other car in
her name too?
>> No, the car is just sitting
on the side -- we was only using
that car because that car was
not registered and it's not
running.
>> Yes, it is.
>> Judge Judy: Oh, so what
you're telling me is the 2011
car is neither registered or
running?
>> No, it's not registered nor
running.
>> Judge Judy: Well, then it
stopped being registered and it
stopped running in what month?
>> Right around the time we got
the Infiniti out.
>> Judge Judy: Oh, there you go.
So it stopped running and it
died, and all of a sudden you
got the money to get it out of
the shop just in time, 'cause
you lost your license.
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Do you have your
license back?
>> No, I'm getting it back in
June.
>> Judge Judy: You can't have
the car back.
>> The car is gone.
She stole the car without my
consent now.
>> Judge Judy: Well, did the
title say "and/or"?
>> It says "and."
>> Judge Judy: Can I see it,
please?
>> She got rid of the car.
She have the title.
We have the slash on it.
But I have another registration
right here.
This is what I got from the DMV
because she took all my
documents when I got
incarcerated.
>> Judge Judy: When you got
incarcerated for what?
>> This is the purpose of her
taking the car because when she
was coming from school, she told
me that she was gonna call the
cops and she's coming to get her
property and she's taking my
car, and I said, "You're not
taking my car.
That's my car.
You're not taking my car."
And when the police pulled up,
they was like, "She's got
possession of the car.
She's taking the car."
I acted stupidly and went out
there and put two tires on flat.
>> Judge Judy: Oh, so you lost
your temper.
>> Yeah.
>> Judge Judy: And you flattened
her tires in front of the
police.
[ Laughter ]
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy"
continues in a moment.
Closed captioning sponsored
by...
Your skin has different
needs at night.
That's why there's new
GOLD BOND overnight lotion.
Works while you sleep,
as hyaluronic acid locks
in moisture.
New GOLD BOND overnight lotion.
>> Announcer: Real cases.
Real people.
"Judge Judy."
>> Judge Judy: Where's the 2011
car, sir?
>> The 2011 car is still on the
side of the road right now.
>> Judge Judy: Well, you can't
drive anyway.
>> I can't drive right now
anyway.
That's why I'm really not
worrying about it.
>> Judge Judy: Is what you're
telling me that you paid to get
the car out of the shop?
>> Yes, ma'am.
I'm actually the one who went
there on the day and handed the
cash to the man who owns the
shop.
His name is Johnny.
>> Judge Judy: So you're telling
me you went there personally, in
August --
>> We were together.
>> Judge Judy: The two of you
together, and you had the cash.
Where did you get the cash from?
>> I took it off of my
BankMobile Vibe card, which is
just a card that the financial
aid uses to disperse your
refund.
>> Judge Judy: Do you have that
card with you?
>> I do.
I don't have any of the
statements printed out, but I do
have the card.
We could call --
>> Judge Judy: If you printed it
out, would it show that you took
money out in August of 2018?
>> Yes, it would.
>> Judge Judy: How much?
>> I believe that it was -- I
had some cash on me, so I
believe it was either $1,100 or
$1,200.
>> Judge Judy: And that would be
on your student-loan card?
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> And I have three receipts
right here.
>> Judge Judy: I'd like to take
a look at them.
Yeah.
>> I believe the signature on
that receipt would be me either
signing his name or my name that
I signed.
It's not his handwriting.
I signed that, and I got the
car.
>> Those are signatures from
Kenny.
>> Oh, well, then that's not the
one when the car was picked up.
>> Judge Judy: Shh, shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh, shh.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
I can't tell who this is.
Anyway --
>> It was paid in three
payments.
I mean, two payments -- paid
$600 one payment, and then
eight-something in another
payment.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care how
much she paid.
Did she pay $1,200?
>> No.
>> Judge Judy: Did she pay
anything?
>> No.
>> Judge Judy: I don't believe
you.
How's that?
I don't believe that she didn't
pay anything.
I actually believe that she paid
something to get your car out.
I don't know if Kenny paid some
and she paid some.
I have no idea.
Kenny messed it up.
She paid it.
She didn't mess it up.
She now has the car.
You do not have the car.
Not only don't you have a car,
you don't have a license, so you
can't drive the car.
Goodbye. We're done.
>> My countersuit?
>> Judge Judy: Your countersuit
is only if you don't get the car
back.
>> Oh, okay.
That's fine.
>> Judge Judy: Perfect.
Goodbye.
>> Byrd: Parties are excused.
You may step out.
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy"
continues in a moment.
And on the next "Judge Judy"...
>> I don't even know, man.
To be honest with you, man, I do
not have the slightest idea.
But I'm gonna let you know right
now that she's really like --
she's vindictive, you know what
I'm saying?
>> The last day of my semester,
I decided I'm leaving, and I'm
not about to just give you
everything that I've worked for
and walk away with nothing.
You can do that to her, but
you're not gonna do that to me.
>> I didn't make her walk or
nothing like that, man.
It's, you know -- I don't know
what made her do it, but I guess
that would probably have saved
my truck if I wouldn't have made
a funny joke or whatever.
>> Yeah, he kind of just, like,
laughed as I was walking off
with all my books.
>> I didn't make no joke.
The girl just walked off acting
some type of way for some
reason.
I don't know what it was, but
I'm out of a truck, out of
$1,500 in cash.
You know what I'm saying?
>> He parked the car around the
corner.
I had to walk super far.
Just little...that he's been
doing.
>> Stay away from her.
She's real vindictive.
I'm for real, man.
Whoever come across her, man,
they gonna find out sooner than
they think.
>> He's really charming in the
beginning, but you'll see the
faultiness as you deal with him,
and he left her for eight
months.
>> But I'm satisfied with it.
The car was sitting on the side
of the road.
The car was trashed to me
anyway.
I'd already had fun in the car.
>> I mean, it's neither here nor
there.
I don't want him.
She can have him.
>> The car is gone.
I'm just glad she ain't driving
around in it.
>> I hope I never see him again.
I hope God deals with him in His
own way, you know?
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
>> Judge Judy: The shortest
distance between two points is
a straight line, not a curve.
>> Announcer: A contractor's
impossible path?
>> We did this driveway this way
to keep the budget intact.
>> Judge Judy: That doesn't
sound logical to me.