>> Announcer: Staying with a
friend was supposed to give her
a fresh start.
>> Judge Judy: You got arrested
when?
>> Two weeks after I moved in.
>> Announcer: It didn't work.
>> There was a suspicion of a
OWI, but no charge.
>> Judge Judy: "OWI" means what?
>> "Operating while
intoxicated."
>> Judge Judy: Have you ever
been in a drug program?
>> No.
>> Judge Judy: Do you need one?
>> I found drug paraphernalia in
the house.
>> That is not true, Your Honor.
>> And the arrest was for her
fifth DUI.
>> Judge Judy: Apparently you
can't get your act together.
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy."
You are about to enter
the courtroom of
Judge Judith Sheindlin.
Captions paid for by
CBS Television Distribution
Melissa Therrian is suing her
former neighbor, Heather Ohlfs,
for stealing her car,
transportation costs, and
unreturned property.
>> Byrd: Order! All rise!
Your Honor, this is case number
362 on the calendar in the
matter of Therrian vs. Ohlfs.
>> Judge Judy: Thank you.
>> Byrd: You're welcome, Judge.
Parties have been sworn in.
You may be seated.
Sir, have a seat, please.
>> Judge Judy: Ms. Therrian, how
do you know the defendant?
>> Ms. Ohlfs is a neighbor of
mine.
She lives across the street from
me for about six years now.
>> Judge Judy: But there came a
time that you moved in to her
home.
>> There is a time when I
moved in.
I moved to Illinois.
Upon moving back from Illinois
to Wisconsin, I resided with my
daughter's father.
It was more comfortable for me
to move in with Ms. Ohlfs.
>> Judge Judy: Okay.
So, you had been neighbors.
Then you moved and then you came
back and when you came back you
needed a place to stay.
>> That's correct.
>> Judge Judy: And what kind of
an arrangement did you make with
regard to paying rent, paying
for utilities?
>> There was no agreement.
There was no rent to be paid,
no utilities.
>> Judge Judy: So, zero rent.
>> Correct.
>> Judge Judy: So, you were
living with her as a friend.
>> As a friend.
>> Judge Judy: Now, you got
arrested when?
>> Shortly after I moved in
the home, two weeks after I
moved in.
>> Judge Judy: And you were
arrested for a DUI.
>> That is not correct.
I was arrested for noncompliance
of vehicle.
The registration for the vehicle
was not the right title of the
plates for the car, and I did
not have a valid driver's
license.
>> Judge Judy: Why didn't you
have a driver's license?
>> I didn't have a driver's
license due to nonpayment of
SR-22 insurance.
>> Judge Judy: It had nothing to
do with a DUI?
>> There's no DUI charges, no.
>> Judge Judy: Did you ever have
a DUI?
>> Years past, 10 years ago,
7 years ago.
>> Judge Judy: Now, your car was
impounded, but your car was
impounded, and you were taken
into custody.
How long were you taken into
custody for?
>> Three days.
>> Judge Judy: And what were the
charges?
>> I had no charges.
I was released due to no
charges.
>> Judge Judy: When they take
you into custody, they have to
book you on a charge.
>> I did receive a refusal after
an arrest for an OWI, but there
was no charge.
>> Judge Judy: No, no, no, no.
"OWI" means what?
>> "Operating while
intoxicated."
>> Judge Judy: Correct.
And you refused to take a
Breathalyzer.
>> I took the Breathalyzer.
I refused the blood.
>> Judge Judy: So, if you
refused the blood draw, you were
taken into custody because they
either suspected that you were
on some sort of drug or alcohol.
>> Correct.
>> Judge Judy: Okay.
So, your car was impounded.
You wanted to get the car out of
impound.
This is what you did.
In order to get a car out of
impound, you have to show that
you're the owner of the car.
You signed over the title to the
defendant.
>> Correct.
>> Judge Judy: The defendant
went and got the car.
You got out of jail three days
later.
Where did you go when you got
out of jail?
>> I went to the defendant's
home, where we were staying.
>> Judge Judy: How long did you
stay there?
>> I was roughly there for about
three weeks.
>> Judge Judy: And during that
three-week time, did you drive
your car?
>> I did drive the vehicle.
>> Judge Judy: Again without a
driver's license.
>> Unfortunately, yes.
>> Judge Judy: Do you have a
driver's license now?
>> Currently I do not.
>> Judge Judy: So, what do you
want the car back for?
>> Basically, I needed the
vehicle -- the finances I can
use to get my license.
I am able to obtain my driver's
license.
>> Judge Judy: I can't order her
to give you back the vehicle.
You've already told me that you
were driving without a license.
You got picked up.
You were held for three days
because you refused to take a
test to determine whether or not
you were under the influence of
some sort of controlled
substance.
You finally got out.
You went back to where you were
living.
The car was there.
You again drove the car without
a license.
You think I'm gonna be party to
giving you back your car?
>> I'm not asking for the car,
ma'am.
I'm asking for the amount of the
vehicle so that I can pay my
driver's license.
>> Judge Judy: That's not gonna
happen.
She's not gonna pay you for the
car.
>> She took my vehicle.
I own the vehicle.
She just took it.
I have title and licensing.
I paid multiple things here.
>> Judge Judy: No, I understand
that you paid for it, but you
turned it over to her.
>> I did not.
>> Judge Judy: I actually --
Yes, you did because you said
you did.
>> With an agreement from her
that she would return the
vehicle to me.
>> Judge Judy: She can't give
you back the car if you're gonna
drive it.
>> I'm not saying that I'm going
to drive it.
I need to sell it financially to
get to my job, so I need to sell
the vehicle.
She sold the vehicle.
It is my vehicle.
I need to sell it for finances.
Basically she took $3,000 out of
my pocket that I can use to
provide for my children.
So, by her taking this
vehicle, me moving --
>> Judge Judy: Shh.
Just a second.
Where are your children?
>> My children are home with
their father.
>> Judge Judy: Okay.
And in what state is their
father?
>> Their father's in Wisconsin,
where I reside with them.
>> Judge Judy: So, is what
you're telling me that you now
live with your children and
their father in Wisconsin?
Is that what you're telling me?
>> That's correct.
>> Judge Judy: Since when?
>> Since I left Ms. Ohlfs' home.
>> Judge Judy: Now, when you
left Wisconsin, where did you
go?
>> I went to Illinois for
multiple -- two years.
>> Judge Judy: And where were
your children when you were in
Illinois?
>> They were with me.
>> Judge Judy: And when you came
back to Wisconsin, why did you
bring the children to their
father and you move in with her?
I'm not following the story.
>> Because I know that the state
of Ms. Ohlfs' being unstable, I
didn't want to bring my children
into the environment that she
lived in.
So therefore I left them with
their father and I moved in and
resided with her temporarily.
We were going to, later down the
road, if she received property
of her home, that we were going
to move my children in and we
were going to fix the home up.
>> Judge Judy: Have you ever
been in a drug program?
>> No.
>> Judge Judy: Do you need one?
>> I do not.
There was no charges on that --
>> Judge Judy: I didn't ask you
whether there were charges.
I'm asking you a question.
>> No, ma'am, I do not.
>> I disagree.
>> Judge Judy: Okay.
I want you to tell me -- She
came and moved in to your house.
And there was some indication in
your answer that, when she moved
out of your house, that there
was some indication of things
that were sort of untoward.
You want to tell me about that?
>> Sure, Your Honor.
Melissa moved in to my home
October 17th of 2018.
I've known Melissa -- it'll be
five years February 25th of
2019.
That's when I closed on my home.
Her children met my children,
okay?
That's where the relationship
began.
>> Judge Judy: Just a second.
This is a very short program.
>> Yes, okay.
>> Judge Judy: I asked you about
what you found in the house.
>> I found drug paraphernalia in
the house.
>> That is not true, Your Honor.
>> Chore Boy and a --
Chore Boy.
>> Judge Judy: What is that?
>> To me, it looks like almost a
Brillo Pad.
It's used to push crack into a
pipe.
>> And how do you know that,
Heather?
>> You told me.
>> That is not mine.
>> [ Chuckles ]
I found it in her room.
So, she told me that Saturday
night she was leaving to go to
work.
She left her daughters at home
with me and my two children.
She left to go, and
approximately noon the following
day, November 5th, we were
worried.
The children were worried.
So I Google up the
Milwaukee County inmate search,
saw that Melissa was, in fact,
in custody and had been taken in
on a DUI.
That's when I need to see what's
going on here.
Her behavior had changed from
when she moved in with me
October 17th until the arrest.
And the arrest was for her
fifth DUI.
So, she's had four priors.
I don't know what happened with
the fifth, but that's what she
was arrested for.
>> Judge Judy: Did she have her
children there with you?
>> The children would come back
and forth.
>> Judge Judy: How old are your
children?
>> They are 12 and 11.
For their stability, I let them
stay with their father.
>> Judge Judy: What happened
with the car?
>> The car -- so, when Melissa
was released from custody, she
came to me and asked if I would
go to the DMV.
She signed the title over, and I
paid for registration, title,
tax, transfer fees
So, we did that because she
could not get it out of impound
without...
>> Judge Judy: A license!
>> ...a license.
>> Judge Judy: She couldn't get
it out without a license.
>> And not only that,
Your Honor -- because of
everything else ordered, because
of these prior DUIs.
So I paid for that...
>> Judge Judy: Don't --
>> ...because she was unable to.
>> Judge Judy: Just a second.
I want you to tell me...
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> Judge Judy: ...what expense
you had in getting the car
out of impound.
>> Impound was $234.
>> Your Honor, I have the
receipt from the tow, as well.
>> Judge Judy: Just a second.
I don't want you to say
anything.
Next. How much?
>> Transfer fees, titles,
registration.
>> Judge Judy: How much?
>> Between $250 and $300.
I do not have those documents
because they were stolen from me
out of my house.
>> Judge Judy: Okay.
And what kind of car do we have?
>> It is a 2002 white
Chrysler Sebring.
>> Judge Judy: Byrd, would you
look that up for me?
Thank you.
>> Your Honor, I also have the
paperwork when I originally
purchased the vehicle.
>> Judge Judy: I don't care.
You have to understand I am
totally unsympathetic with you.
>> I apologize.
>> Judge Judy: I think that
you've made a whole lot of bad
mistakes in your life, and I
really don't care about you.
I care about your two children
who are 11 and 12, who hop from
one place to another because
apparently you can't get your
act together.
>> No, I do have my act
together.
Those were from multiple years
ago, ma'am.
There is no charge now.
I have not had an OWI in seven
years.
That was the past, before my
children, before they started
growing up and needing me.
I am here now to show them --
And Ms. Ohlfs has been --
>> Judge Judy: Just a s--
You went to Illinois.
You took your children -- Their
father was in Wisconsin.
You brought them back form
Illinois.
Now you --
>> They've been jostled around
and --
>> Judge Judy: Just a second.
>> I apologize.
>> Judge Judy: You're not
following it.
>> I am, ma'am.
>> Judge Judy: That's shorter
distance in time than seven
years ago.
>> That is their stability
there, and that's where I reside
with them, as well.
We are all together as a family.
>> Judge Judy: Oh, that's great.
>> And, Your Honor, I'd like to
point out Ms. Ohlfs also has a
drug-and-alcohol issue.
She has been in multiple drug
programs.
She is currently on a DPA, so
her actions, as well -- I
believe she stole the vehicle to
sell for her drug habit.
>> Judge Judy: That's just
wonderful.
That only suggests to me,
actually, Ms. Therrian, that
when you said to me before you
wanted the children to have more
stability -- so, you took them
to her house?
>> No, I did not bring them to
her house.
>> Judge Judy: [ Laughs ] Okay.
>> No, I did not bring them
there.
>> Byrd: Okay, Judge, the price
range is $360 to $649.
>> Your Honor, Melissa's
allegation of me being a drug
addict --
>> Judge Judy: Just a second.
>> Okay. I know.
>> Judge Judy: It's not even
there.
>> Yeah.
>> Judge Judy: It's not there.
It's gone. It's gone.
>> I agree.
>> Judge Judy: Now, you want to
tell me about the broken windows
and the threatening text on
January 6th that you got from
her?
>> So, on January 5th, Scott,
who is here with me on my
behalf, went to my home to get
some items for me.
Upon arrival, he discovered a
broken kitchen window.
I have pictures of all of this.
>> Judge Judy: Okay, so you have
a broken kitchen window.
>> Broken kitchen window.
>> Judge Judy: And?
>> He came, picked me up from
his house.
I started opening blinds in my
home, and there were four broken
windows, smashed, shattered, on
the south side of my house.
>> Judge Judy: Okay.
How do you connect that to her?
>> Because I received two text
messages.
>> Judge Judy: I'd like to see
them.
>> You got it.
>> I hope I'm not being in
connection in any of this at
all.
I would not do damage to your
home, Heather, no matter how mad
I am at you.
You know that.
>> Here's the photos.
>> Judge Judy: I don't want the
photos.
I want the text messages.
>> Here you are, Your Honor.
They're highlighted.
>> Your Honor, I would not do
anything of any sort.
That's childish behavior.
I would not do anything, no
damage to her home.
I'm trying to claim my vehicle
back for the value so I can
sell it.
>> Judge Judy: You're not
getting your vehicle back.
I'm not giving a vehicle back to
somebody who's been driving
without a license.
Your vehicle's worth 500 bucks.
She paid $234 to get your car
out of impound.
You paid her no money when you
and your children were living
there for a month.
You're even.
>> I got it on my --
>> Judge Judy: We're done.
Thank you.
>> Byrd: Parties are excused.
You may step out.
>> Oh, absolutely, she
definitely betrayed.
>> It's absolutely insulting.
>> She betrayed it by
manipulating.
>> Because I opened my door to
her.
>> Just leaving somebody out in
the cold in the winter.
>> She didn't pay me rent.
She didn't pay for any
utilities.
>> Me and my two daughters were
left out in the cold.
>> And I was offering her help.
>> I just hope we can move on.
>> We have burned the bridge.
>> Announcer: And now the next
case.
>> Byrd: All parties in the
matter of Owen vs. Benschoter,
step forward.
>> Announcer: Scott Owen is
suing his daughter's boyfriend,
Tyler Benschoter, for a $1,400
loan to fix his truck.
>> Judge Judy: Mr. Owen, it is
your claim that the defendant
owes you for a loan that you
made to him to fix his car.
And at the time that you made
this loan to him, he was your
daughter's boyfriend.
>> Yeah, they were seeing each
other on and off, yes.
>> Judge Judy: Are you still
seeing each other?
>> We are still together.
>> Judge Judy: And she's your
witness?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Okay.
So, I'm gonna start with you,
sir.
What do you do for a living?
>> I'm a machine operator that
makes plastic.
>> Judge Judy: Are you married?
>> No.
>> Judge Judy: Do you have
children?
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: How many?
>> One.
>> Judge Judy: How old?
>> 8.
>> Judge Judy: Who do you live
with?
>> Myself.
>> Judge Judy: In an apartment
or a house?
>> A house.
>> Judge Judy: Where do you
live?
>> I live in a Winnebago by
myself.
Oh.
>> Judge Judy: Who do you work
for?
>> St. Luke's Lutheran Care
Center.
>> Judge Judy: Did you ask your
father for money to fix your
boyfriend's truck?
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy"
continues in a moment.
>> Judge Judy: What were you
gonna be in contact with him
for, to say --
>> To find out what I was gonna
do in order to make things right
with him.
>> Judge Judy: Make things right
how?
You were gonna plow his driveway
for five years?
What were you gonna do
to make it right?
>> Announcer: Closed captioning
is provided by...
Every baby can have the freedom
to move their way In Pampers
Cruisers
with
three-way fit
They adapt at the waist, legs
and bottom
for all the freedom
to move their way
Pampers
For mild-to-moderate eczema,
there's EUCRISA.
It's steroid-free.
Do not use if you are allergic
to EUCRISA or its ingredients.
Allergic reactions may occur
at or near the application site.
The most common side effect
is application site pain.
Ask your doctor about EUCRISA.
>> Announcer: Real cases.
Real people.
"Judge Judy."
Scott Owen says his daughter's
boyfriend, Tyler Benschoter,
owes for a loan to fix his
truck.
>> Judge Judy: Now, did you ask
TEST
>> Judge Judy: How much did your
boyfriend need?
>> $1,400.
>> Judge Judy: And between the
two of you working, you didn't
TEST TEST
>> Judge Judy: When you first
asked your father for this
money, what did he say?
>> He had asked me if there was
anybody else that could borrow
the money to him.
>> Judge Judy: Just a second.
You borrow money.
You lend someone money.
>> Okay, well, someone to lend
him money.
And I just didn't know anybody
else to ask, and so that's when
I asked my dad.
>> Judge Judy: Well, tell me
about the conversation.
Tell me what you said to him and
what he said to you.
>> I had just gone into his
bedroom at the time and asked
him if he would lend Tyler the
$1,400 for his truck to be
fixed.
And at that time, that's when he
had wrote a check, and I had
brought it to Tyler and gave it
to him.
>> Judge Judy: Okay.
And I'd like you to tell me what
you told to your boyfriend when
you got the check in your hand.
>> I called him and told him
that I had a check that my dad
had wrote to his mechanic to fix
his truck and that I would meet
him where his truck was.
And then that's when I had given
it to him.
>> Judge Judy: Now, your father
made it clear to you, based upon
what you told me, that he
expected your boyfriend to pay
him back.
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Did you make that
clear to your boyfriend?
>> Yes, I did.
>> Judge Judy: At what point did
you make that clear to him?
>> When I had called him and
told him.
>> Judge Judy: So, I want you to
tell me that part of the
conversation, which you left
out.
>> I had called Tyler and told
him that my dad had wrote him a
check and that he would need to
be paying my dad back.
>> Judge Judy: And what did he
say to you?
>> He said that he would be in
contact with my dad to discuss
the payment agreement.
>> Judge Judy: Does that sound
familiar to you?
>> Some of it.
I did say that I would be in
contact with him.
>> Judge Judy: What were you
gonna be in contact with him
for?
>> About the money that I
received for my pickup.
>> Judge Judy: What were you
gonna be in contact with him
for, to say --
>> To find out what we would do
further with --
>> Judge Judy: What did you
think you would do further?
Did you think he was gonna give
you more money?
What were you gonna be in touch
with him --
>> To figure out what we were
gonna as --
>> Judge Judy: Not "what we were
gonna do."
He already did it.
>> Okay -- what I was gonna do
in order to make things right
with him.
>> Judge Judy: Make things right
how?
You were gonna plow his driveway
for five years?
You were going to dig him a new
basement?
What were you gonna do to make
it right?
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy"
continues in a moment.
>> What you just said to me
didn't happen.
It wasn't said.
Tell me something I believe,
Tyler, 'cause so far you're
dancing around.
>> It was a -- It was --
If you don't mind -- Okay.
>> Judge Judy: I'm having too
good a time.
>> All right.
[ Laughter ]
You know that look?
That life of the party look.
Walk it off look.
One more mile look.
Reply all look.
Own your look with fewer lines.
There's only one
BOTOX® COSMETIC.
It's the only one FDA approved
to temporarily make
frown lines,
crow's feet and forehead
lines look better.
The effects of BOTOX® COSMETIC
may spread hours to weeks
after injection,
causing serious symptoms.
Alert your doctor right away
as difficulty swallowing,
speaking, breathing,
eye problems,
or muscle weakness
may be a sign of
a life-threatening condition.
Do not receive BOTOX® COSMETIC
if you have a skin infection.
Side effects may include
allergic reactions,
injection site pain, headache,
eyebrow, eyelid drooping
and eyelid swelling.
Tell your doctor about
your medical history,
muscle or nerve conditions,
and medications
including botulinum toxins
as these may increase the risk
of serious side effects.
So, give that
just saw a puppy look
and whatever that look is.
Look like you with fewer lines.
Own your look
with the one and only
BOTOX® COSMETIC.
>> Announcer: Real cases.
Real people.
"Judge Judy."
Scott Owen says his daughter's
boyfriend, Tyler Benschoter,
owes for a loan to fix his
truck.
>> Judge Judy: Now, what were
you gonna do to make it right?
>> That's what we were going to
discuss.
>> Judge Judy: And did you ever
make that call?
>> I talked with him very
briefly once.
>> Judge Judy: I want you to
tell me that brief call.
Did you call him, or did he call
you?
>> Actually, I was standing in
his living room.
>> Judge Judy: So, there was no
call.
You were actually face-to-face.
>> Yes.
>> Judge Judy: Now you're
standing face-to-face.
What's the conversation?
He asked if I would be able to
pay him back, and I told him
there would be nothing exchanged
until after this work trip.
>> Judge Judy: That doesn't
sound like normal conversation.
Tyler, that's not normal
conversation -- "There would be
nothing exchanged before
after --" That doesn't sound
like -- You either say, "I'll
have money for you when I come
back from this trip.
You know, I can start paying
you."
But what you just said to me
didn't happen.
It wasn't said.
You want to tell me your version
of what was said before I ask
Mr. Owen his version?
Tell me something I believe,
Tyler, 'cause so far you're
dancing around and you're
dancing around.
And instead of saying, "Somebody
made a nice gesture, somebody
who is not related to me,
somebody who probably doesn't
even like me made a gesture" --
And it was made clear to you
before you took the check by her
that you had to pay her father
back.
That's what she said.
So, before you took the check,
you knew you had to do that.
Very easy.
You knew it wasn't a gift.
So, now you're standing in front
of him in his living room,
and...?
>> I told him, "Thank you," and
then he asked about the trip
that I was supposed to make.
And the conversation ended.
>> Judge Judy: Well, you just
told me during the
conversation -- the words you
used, "When we were gonna be
[chuckling] able to exchange
money."
>> It was a -- It was --
If you don't mind -- Okay.
>> Judge Judy: I'm having too
good a time.
>> All right.
[ Laughter ]
>> Judge Judy: When did you
discuss repayment with him?
>> The only time I ever called
is when I got a text message
from him demanding I had like
seven days to give it to him.
>> Judge Judy: Did you say, "I
can write you a check this week
for 10 bucks, just as a showing
of good faith, and I'll make a
payment of $40 a month until I'm
paid up"?
>> No, I did not.
>> Judge Judy: Why not?
>> Never discussed --
>> Judge Judy: Because a gesture
of, "I know I owe you this
money, but right now it's a
little tight," is what you do.
Otherwise, you're a bum.
And that's why people don't do
nice things for other people.
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy"
continues in a moment.
Closed captioning
sponsored by...
Why let itchy irritated
skin keep you
from all the
fun this winter.
Cortizone-10 works fast
to help soothe irritation
and relieve itch
for 10 full hours.
Cortizone-10.
>> Announcer: Real cases.
Real people.
"Judge Judy."
>> Judge Judy: Find yourself
another guy.
If he got between you and your
father, find yourself another
guy.
I want you to look to your
right.
What's immediately on your
right?
>> Tyler.
>> Judge Judy: In five years,
he's gonna be gone.
You think the mother of his
8-year-old thought it was gonna
be forever?
>> Yeah.
>> Judge Judy: You now
understand his character.
If you look further to your
right, that's your father.
He's gonna be there forever.
You know, there's a line from
"The Godfather," but it really
is very important -- never take
sides with someone against your
family.
Five years, you won't remember
what he looks like.
You owe him $1,400.
Judgment for the plaintiff.
We're done.
>> Byrd: Parties are excused.
You may step out.
>> Announcer: "Judge Judy"
continues in a moment.
And on the next "Judge Judy"...
>> You know what?
I've known him since he was a
little kid, and I've never had a
problem with him.
>> Strongly disagree with what
she came up with today.
>> But I'm at a spot in my life
where I pay a lot of child
support.
>> 'Cause he is in a strong
spot, like he said.
>> And I need the money, too,
and I did what I needed to do to
get it back.
>> I just feel like I don't owe
him anything.
>> Well, after today it's
just -- it's between those
two...
>> It has definitely made a
hardship for a lot of things...
>> ...you know, what they want
to do with the rest of their
lives.
>> ...'cause things have been
very rocky and personal things
have gone on, so...
>> I can't be a part of it.
I can just pray and, you know,
hope that things work out.
>> I think everything will be
okay.
We have a pretty strong bond and
relationship the way it is.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
We have a pretty strong bond and
relationship the way it is.
>> RIGHT NOW AT 5, RALPH
NORTHAM REFUSING TO RESIGN AND
POSSIBLE SUCCESSOR FACING A
SCANDAL OF HIS OWN AND STATE
ATTORNEY GENERAL ADMITS HE
WORN BLACK FACE AS WELL.
WE HAVE LIVE TEAM COVERAGE.
>> AND WILLED VIDEO OF A U.S.
PARK POLICE CHOPPER CHASING
PEOPLE PLAYING ICE HOCKEY OFF
THE REFLECTING POOL.
YOUR NEWS STARTS NOW.
♪
>> FIRST AT 5:00.
STARTLING REVELATIONS TODAY
OUT OF VIRGINIA WHERE STATE
ATTORNEY GENERAL NOW ADMITS HE
TOO, HAS WORN BACK FACE.
>> AND WOMAN ACCUSED JUSTIN
FAIRFAX OF SEXUAL ASSAULT
COMING FORWARD WITH HER
DETAILED ALLEGATIONS.
THE TOP THREE STATE ELECTED
OFFICIALS IN THE COMMONWEALTH
ARE EMBROILED IN SCANDAL AND
ASKED TO RESIGN.
JOSH.
HAS THE LATEST.
>> JIM, HOW DO YOU EVEN BEGIN
JOSH.
TO EXPLAIN WHAT IS IT GOING ON
>> JIM, HOW DO YOU EVEN BEGIN
RIGHT NOW IN VIRGINIA.
TO EXPLAIN WHAT IS IT GOING ON
JUST TO BE CLEAR, HERE'S THE
RIGHT NOW IN VIRGINIA.
SCENARIO WE'RE WORKING WITH.
JUST TO BE CLEAR, HERE'S THE
GOVERNOR, HAS A BLACK FACE
SCENARIO WE'RE WORKING WITH.
SCANDAL.
GOVERNOR, HAS A BLACK FACE
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR ACCUSED OF
SCANDAL.
SEXUAL ASSAULT AND ATTORNEY
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR ACCUSED OF
GENERAL SAYS HE HAS WORN BLACK
SEXUAL ASSAULT AND ATTORNEY
FACE BEFORE, TOO.
GENERAL SAYS HE HAS WORN BLACK
>> WEDNESDAY VIRGINIA ATTORNEY
FACE BEFORE, TOO.
GENERAL MARK HERRING RELEASED
>> WEDNESDAY VIRGINIA ATTORNEY
THIS SAME IN 1980 WHEN 19 IN
GENERAL MARK HERRING RELEASED
CLEM HE AND FRIENDS WANTED TO
THIS SAME IN 1980 WHEN 19 IN
ATTEND A PARTY DRESSED LIKE
CLEM HE AND FRIENDS WANTED TO
RAPPERS AND WANTED TO PERFORM
ATTEND A PARTY DRESSED LIKE
A SONG.
RAPPERS AND WANTED TO PERFORM
SO HE SAID THEY "PUT ON WIGS
A SONG.
AND BROWN MAKEUP.
SO HE SAID THEY "PUT ON WIGS
AND HERRING GOES ON TO SAY IT
AND BROWN MAKEUP.
WAS ONE TIME OWE KURPS ADDING
AND HERRING GOES ON TO SAY IT
THAT CONDUCT CLEARLY SHOWS AS
WAS ONE TIME OWE KURPS ADDING
A YOUNG MAN HI A CALLOUS AND
THAT CONDUCT CLEARLY SHOWS AS
INEXCUSABLE LACK OF AWARENESS
A YOUNG MAN HI A CALLOUS AND
AND INSENSITIVITY TO THE PAIN
INEXCUSABLE LACK OF AWARENESS
MIB HAIVR COULD INFLICT IN
AND INSENSITIVITY TO THE PAIN
OTHERS AND IT WAS
MIB HAIVR COULD INFLICT IN
AMINIMIZIO