TELL ME WHAT DEVIL
GOT INTO YOUR HANDS
AND MADE YOU ATTACK
YOUR TEACHER!
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND, MA.
MAKE ME.
ANNOUNCER: A DEDICATED
INNER-CITY HIGH SCHOOL TEACHER
STRUGGLES TO SAVE HER SON
FROM AN EDUCATIONAL SYSTEM THAT
SEEMS RIGGED AGAINST HIM.
THEY DON'T CARE WHAT
SPACE AND PLACE I'M IN.
HE SAID HE DIDN'T
SLAM THAT TEACHER,
BUT ON THE VIDEO--
THERE'S A VIDEO?
HE'S NOT A CRIMINAL.
WOMAN: TELL ME
HOW TO SAVE YOU.
TELL ME WHAT WOULD TAKE
THIS FAILURE AWAY.
WOMAN: DUN!
GET THE NURSE NOW!
ANNOUNCER: "PIPELINE," TONIGHT
ON "LIVE FROM LINCOLN CENTER."
GOOD MORNING, CLASS.
ANNOUNCER:
"LIVE FROM LINCOLN CENTER"
IS MADE POSSIBLE
BY THE FAMILY OF
ROBERT WOOD JOHNSON III--
DEDICATED TO ENRICHING THE LIVES
OF ALL AMERICANS
THROUGH MEDICAL RESEARCH,
EDUCATION, AND THE ARTS--
THE ROBERT AND RENEE BELFER
FAMILY FOUNDATION;
MERCEDES T. BASS;
AND THE NATIONAL ENDOWMENT
FOR THE ARTS.
MAJOR SUPPORT FOR THIS EPISODE
IS PROVIDED BY THE DORIS DUKE
CHARITABLE FOUNDATION.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
HEY. IT'S--IT'S ME.
I KNOW I SH--SHOULDN'T,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO...
WE NEED TO TALK.
IT'S ABOUT OUR SON.
HE GOT INTO A FIGHT
ON SCHOOL GROUNDS.
THEY'RE GONNA--
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT--
THEY'RE TALKING
KICKING HIM OUT.
THEY'RE
TALKING PRESSING CHARGES.
THEY'RE GONNA--
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE
GONNA--I'M JUST--
I'M EXHAUSTED, YOU KNOW THAT?
LIKE THERE'S NO MORE HELIUM.
I'M SINKING.
LIKE THERE'S ALL THIS WEIGHT.
CAN'T FIGHT GRAVITY.
YOU KNOW?
I CAN'T EVEN FIGHT
THIS PULLING DOWN.
IT'S TAKING ALL M--
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW.
SO--ANYWAY,
GIVE ME A CALL WHEN YOU GET THIS
SO WE CAN TALK.
TALK ABOUT YOUR SON.
OUR SON. US.
YEAH. OK.
FINE. UM...
I ALSO MISS YOU.
OH, I SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID THAT.
SHOULD DELETE THAT.
GONNA DELETE THAT.
[BEEP]
VOICE ON PHONE: TO ERASE
AND RE-RECORD, PRESS 3.
TO CONTINUE RECORDING
WHERE YOU LEFT OFF, PRESS 4.
[BEEP]
HEY, XAVIER, IT'S NYA,
CALLING TO TALK ABOUT OUR SON.
GIVE ME A CALL
WHEN YOU GET THIS.
THANKS. BYE.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
WOMAN ON P.A.:
GOOD MORNING, STUDENTS.
WELCOME TO ANOTHER GLORIOUS DAY
AT CHADSEY HIGH.
PLEASE REMEMBER
TO TAKE OFF YOUR HATS.
NO SAGGING ALLOWED.
NEW POLICY IN EFFECT TODAY:
HOMEROOM TEACHERS ARE NOW
GOING TO LOCK YOUR CELL PHONES
AND OTHER NON-SCHOOL-ISSUED
DEVICES IN THEIR DRAWERS.
YOU WILL RETRIEVE THEM
AT THE END OF THE DAY.
IF YOU HAVE
ANY OBJECTIONS TO THIS,
THEN YOU ARE FREE TO LEAVE
YOUR DEVICES AT HOME.
IF YOU ARE CAUGHT
WITH ANY NON-APPROVED
ELECTRONIC DEVICE IN CLASS,
THIS IS AN AUTOMATIC SUSPENSION.
NO EXCEPTIONS.
I REPEAT: NO EXCEPTIONS!
PLEASE DO NOT HAVE
YOUR MAMAS COMING UP HERE
DEMANDING TO GET YOUR
SMARTPHONES BACK.
WE HAVE THE CITY GOVERNMENT
BEHIND US.
YOU CANNOT WIN.
I REPEAT: YOU CANNOT WIN!
ALSO, THERE'S A PEP RALLY
TODAY AFTER SCHOOL.
BE SURE TO ATTEND
AND SHOW YOUR SCHOOL PRIDE.
AND FINALLY,
HAVE A GLORIOUS DAY, STUDENTS.
A GLORIOUS DAY.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
GOOD MORNING, CLASS.
ALL: GOOD MORNING.
[LAUGHTER]
PULL OUT YOUR PENS.
POP QUIZ TODAY.
TELL ME YOU WASN'T
LOOKIN' AT HER!
I WASN'T LOOKIN' AT HER.
I OUGHT
TO CUT HER FACE.
I WASN'T
LOOKIN' AT HER.
THINKIN' SHE'S
SO CUTE.
I WASN'T LOOKIN'
AT HER.
SHE'S NOT
THAT CUTE.
I WAS KINDA
LOOKIN' AT HER.
WHAT?
JUST LIKE
A LITTLE BIT.
WHAT'S A LITTLE BIT?
LIKE MODESTLY.
WITH NO INTENTION.
JUST OBSERVING.
WHAT YOU GOT TO BE
OBSERVING FOR?
TO TAKE IN
MY SURROUNDINGS.
LEARN THE WORLD.
NOT BE JUST TIED UP
IN MY OWN EXISTENCE
AND NOTHING ELSE.
EVERYTHING'S MORE
IMPORTANT TO YOU
THAN ME.
YOU IMPORTANT
TO ME.
NOT HARDLY.
YOU JUST
BIDING YOUR TIME
TILL YOU FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO DO NEXT.
AIN'T THAT IT?
WHY WOULD YOU
SAY THAT?
'CAUSE I DON'T LIKE
TO TALK AT NOTHIN'.
I LIKE TO SAY
EXACTLY WHAT'S WHAT.
YOU WANNA KNOW
WHAT'S WHAT?
YEAH, I WANNA KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE I'M GONNA BE
TWO DAYS FROM NOW
OR TWO HOURS.
AND I CAN'T
BE PRETENDING
WE IN SOME
FAIRY-TALE FANTASY
WHERE ALL I NEED TO DO
IS CHILL WITH YOU
IN A CASTLE WITH OUR
HORSES OR WHATEVER.
HORSES?
OR WHATEVER.
I DON'T KNOW.
WHATEVER THEY GOT
IN CASTLES.
TRUTH IS, I GOT
TOO MANY WORRIES,
AND BEIN' WITH YOU
DON'T MAKE 'EM GO NOWHERE.
YOU FEEL ME?
YOU SAYING I'M ADDING
TO YOUR STRESS LEVEL?
I'M SAYING
I GOT STRESSES.
REAL ONES.
AND HIDING OUT
IN YOUR DORM ROOM
AIN'T DOIN' NOTHIN' BUT
PROLONGING THE INEVITABLE.
THIS SOME WACK VERSION
OF A BREAKUP?
IT'S JUST ME
BEING HONEST.
WELL, ... YOUR HONESTY.
SERIOUSLY, OMARI,
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE
MY HEART EXPLODE
WITH ALL YOUR
BACK-AND-FORTHNESS.
ONE MINUTE YOU
TELLIN' ME I'M THE CURE,
NEXT I'M THE CAUSE?
MAYBE YOU'RE YOUR
OWN STRESS PROBLEM
AND I AIN'T GOT
NOTHIN' TO DO
WITH IT.
MAYBE I AM.
... YOU.
MAYBE I'M CONFUSED.
THAT'S THE REALEST ...
YOU EVER SAID.
YO! THIS COULD BE
OUR LAST TIME.
YOU KIDDIN' ME
RIGHT NOW?
I'M JUST
SEEKING INTIMACY.
YOU SEEKING TO GET
SOCKED IN THE EYE.
I DON'T TURN ON
AND OFF LIKE NO STOVE.
YOU MEAN A FAUCET.
I MEAN A STOVE.
ONE MINUTE,
YOU GOT ME HOT,
NEXT MINUTE,
FIRE'S OUT.
QUIT GASSING ME UP
AND KILLING
MY ... SPARK.
CAN'T NOTHING
KILL YOUR SPARK.
YOU ALWAYS
GONNA BE FIRE.
AND YOU ALWAYS
DRIVE ME CRAZY.
I'M SCARED.
WHY YOU FIGHT HIM, O?
WHY YOU SAY YOU GONNA
CUT KEELY'S FACE?
'CAUSE SHE THINKS
SHE CUTE.
SO, YOU WANNA
MESS THAT UP?
MAYBE IT WOULD MAKE
THINGS BALANCED.
LIKE WHAT?
LIKE SHE WEAR
ON THE OUTSIDE
WHAT I FEEL ON
THE INSIDE.
THAT'S MESSED UP.
SO?
I'M MESSED UP.
YOUR MOMS KNOWS?
SHE PROBABLY ALREADY
PLANNING HER SPEECH.
THREATENING TO SEND ME
TO MY POPS,
BUT DUDE WOULDN'T GO FOR
THAT IN A MILLION YEARS.
YOU AIN'T SUPPOSED
TO EVEN BE HERE
RIGHT NOW.
IF ANYBODY
FINDS US--
WHERE ELSE
CAN WE MEET?
THEY WON'T LET ME
TALK TO YOU
ANYWHERE ON
THE CAMPUS.
SUPPOSED TO BE PACKING
MY STUFF TO GO HOME.
AIN'T LIKE I
COULD VISIT YOU
BACK AT YOUR
FOLKS' CRIB.
THEY WON'T LET ME
NOWHERE NEAR YOU.
TEEN PREGNANCY STATS
GOT 'EM SPOOKED.
THEY DON'T KNOW
WHO OR WHAT I AM.
I KNOW WHAT YOU ARE.
YOU DON'T KNOW YOURSELF.
HOW YOU KNOW ME?
I KNOW YOU.
WHAT YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE A METAMORPHIC ROCK.
HERE WE GO!
WHAT?
SCIENCE REFERENCES FROM
MR. PETERSON'S CLASS
AIN'T GONNA SAVE YOU
FROM MY WRATH.
NOT TRYING TO GET SAVED.
JUST MAKING
AN OBSERVATION.
EXPLAIN.
METAMORPHIC ROCKS.
THEY CHANGE IN FORM,
MADE FROM HEAT
AND PRESSURE.
THAT'S WHAT
MAKES THEM SO RARE
AND INTERESTING.
AND THAT'S ME?
THAT'S YOU.
I THINK I'M
IN LOVE WITH YOU.
I THINK I'M LEAVING.
WHERE YOU GO?
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
I GOT SOME
MONEY SAVED.
CHILD SUPPORT STASH
FROM THE OLD MAN.
... ADDS UP WHEN
YOU DON'T SPEND IT.
SO, YOU JUST
GONNA RUN AWAY
FROM YOUR PROBLEMS?
WHAT ELSE
I'M GONNA DO?
STAY AND LET 'EM
TAKE AWAY
MY LIFE, MY FUTURE?
MAYBE NOT.
THEY RECORDED IT.
SO, THREATEN ANYBODY
WHO PUT IT UP.
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO TRACE IT.
IF IT GOES VIRAL,
I'M A WRAP,
AND IT'S GONNA
GO VIRAL.
... IT THEN.
YOU'LL BE
A CELEBRITY.
I'LL BE PUBLIC ENEMY
NUMBER ONE.
YOU WON'T.
I'LL BE A MONSTER.
YOU'LL BE THAT ...
THAT NOBODY WILL
... WITH.
THAT AIN'T THE LEGACY
I WAS TRYING TO LEAVE.
WHAT LEGACY YOU
GONNA LEAVE NOW?
RUNNIN' AWAY?
I JUST GOTTA
GO, JASMINE.
I KNOW WHAT YOU ARE.
WHAT AM I?
A LUNAR ECLIPSE.
HOW'S THAT?
RARE. AND HIDING
IN THE SHADOWS
OF THE EARTH,
ALWAYS READY
FOR AN ESCAPE.
MR. PETERSON'S
SCIENCE CLASS
IS THE BEST.
DON'T LEAVE.
THINK I GOTTA.
I CAN'T SURVIVE THIS
PREP ... WITHOUT YOU.
YOU CAN
SURVIVE ANYTHING.
DON'T LEAVE.
CAN I KISS YOU
ONE LAST TIME?
MAKE IT LAST FOREVER.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
... FIFTH PERIOD.
TURN IN YOUR REPORTS?
NOT YET.
HUMPHREYS IS
ON MY ASS.
ENGLISH DEPARTMENT
HEAD OR NOT,
I TOLD HIM TO GIVE ME
A DAMN BREAK.
I ONLY JUST HAD MY FACE
RECONSTRUCTED. ...
YOU LOOK GOOD, LAURIE.
I CAN'T EVEN TELL.
MY HUSBAND CAN.
AND MY DAUGHTER.
I FREAK HER OUT,
SHE SAYS.
WELL, EVERYTHING
FREAKS HER OUT
THAT ISN'T PAINTED
WITH AT LEAST
A GAZILLION OUNCES
OF MASCARA,
OR LITERS
OR HOWEVER THE ...
YOU MEASURE MASCARA.
SHE'S ... OBSESSED
WITH IT.
THAT'S ALL I KNOW.
I MEAN, WHAT
THE HELL HAPPENED
TO TEENAGEHOOD?
I REMEMBER DYEING
MY HAIR ORANGE
AND PIERCING MY NOSE
TO RAGE AGAINST
THE STATUS QUO,
BUT THAT WAS A SORT
OF CAUSE, YOU KNOW?
NOWADAYS, IT'S JUST
MASCARA AND FASHION
AND NEXT TOP SUPERMODEL
HOUSEWIVES OF
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
I MEAN, WHAT THE HELL
ARE WE DOING, YOU KNOW?
ARE THEY GROWING
DOWN?
PROBABLY.
AND THE SUBSTITUTE
WAS AN IDIOT.
I ASKED MY KIDS,
"WHAT'D YOU DO
WHILE I WAS GONE?"
3 WEEKS WHILE
I WAS GONE.
YOU KNOW,
NOT ONE OF THEM
COULD GIVE ME
A STRAIGHT ANSWER.
THEN ALEJANDRO
FINALLY CRACKS.
WATCHED "THE WIRE."
SEASON 4,
HE TELLS ME.
"THE WIRE"?
YEAH. SAYS
THE SUB WAS
TRYING TO SHOW 'EM
WHAT NOT TO DO.
ARE YOU ...
KIDDING ME?
WHICH SUB WAS THIS?
THAT CUTE YOUNG BLONDE
STRAIGHT OUT OF
TEACHER'S COLLEGE.
PATRICIA OR PATRICE
OR SOME ... .
I MEAN, WHAT
THE HELL ARE THEY
TEACHING THEM
OVER THERE?
THE LAST SUB
THEY SENT ME
SHOWED 'EM
"DANGEROUS MINDS."
DO THEY REALLY
BELIEVE THAT
PUBLIC SCHOOL IS
MICHELLE PFEIFFER
AND HILARY SWANK
AND CORNY ... MUSIC
AND CLOSE-UPS?
I AM A WHITE CHICK
WHO HAS NEVER
HAD THE LUXURY
OF WINNING OVER
A CLASS FULL OF
BLACK AND LATINO KIDS.
THIS IS WAR.
I GOT MY ...
FACE CUT
BY THE FAMILY OF
A FAILING STUDENT.
... THEM
AND THEIR LIES
AND THESE SUBSTITUTES
WHO SHOW THESE DUMBASS,
GODFORSAKEN,
SETTING US BACK
300 EDUCATIONAL YEARS,
BULL-... FLICKS.
TEACH, YOU ...
I LEFT YOU LESSON
PLANS, FOR ... SAKE.
YEAH.
THEY SHOULD'VE
GOTTEN YOU SMITH.
HUH?
SHE'S A SUBSTITUTE TEACHER
FROM THE GODS.
THAT WEEK I WAS GONE
WITH OMARI'S PNEUMONIA,
I CAME BACK, MY KIDS
HAD ALREADY MOVED ON
TO THE NEXT CHAPTER
OF "INVISIBLE MAN."
PAPERS WERE GRADED
AND EVERYTHING.
IT WAS IMPRESSIVE.
AN ENIGMA
IN THIS PLACE.
YOU GONNA RETIRE
OR WHAT?
OH, ... THEM
AND THEIR RETIREMENT.
THEY'RE NOT GONNA
FORCE MY HAND.
TRY TO MOVE ME
FROM 9th GRADE TO
10th GRADE TO 12th.
I'LL OUTLAST 'EM ALL.
BASTARDS.
YOU'RE A PISTOL, WOMAN.
I'M A GODDAMN
MACHINE GUN.
HOW'S YOUR SON?
TROUBLE.
NEXT QUESTION.
YOU FIGURED OUT WHAT
YOU'RE GONNA DO ABOUT--
HAVEN'T FIGURED OUT
A THING.
I'M SLIPPING OFF
THE EDGE OF THE EARTH.
THERE'S NO ANSWER IN
THE DARK, DARK UNIVERSE.
THE WORLD ISN'T
FLAT, NYA.
MINE IS, LAURIE.
IT'S FLAT.
IT'S COMING TO
A QUICK AND FAST END,
AND I CAN'T STOP IT.
YES, YOU CAN.
YOU JUST GOTTA
GRAB IT BY THE BALLS
AND TURN IT AROUND.
THAT SON OF YOURS
NEEDS A SWIFT KICK
IN THE ASS.
THAT'S NOT WHAT
HE NEEDS, LAURIE.
I REMEMBER
WHEN PARENTS
USED TO GIVE US
PERMISSION TO SPANK
THEIR KIDS IN CLASS.
YOU OLD ENOUGH
TO REMEMBER THAT?
WE TEACH TEENAGERS.
ESPECIALLY
THE TEENAGERS.
YEAH, I DON'T THINK
I REMEMBER THAT.
THAT WAS THE BEST.
I'M TELLING YOU.
I HAD THIS ONE KID.
LOUIE GASPACHO.
I REMEMBER HIM
REAL GOOD.
YOU KNOW HOW SOME OF
THEM STAY WITH YOU
FOR A LIFETIME?
WELL, HE HAD KIND OF
A SCHIZOPHRENIA
THING GOING ON.
UNDIAGNOSED,
BUT I KNEW.
YOU KNOW,
THEY SHOULD LET US
PRESCRIBE THE DRUGS
INSTEAD OF THESE
BOGUS DOCTORS.
I KNOW THESE KIDS
INSIDE AND OUT.
I KNEW LOUIE.
ANOTHER KID I THINK
RITALIN RUINED.
BUT HIS FOLKS
LISTENED TO THAT
SORRY EXCUSE
OF A COUNSELOR--
MS. ESSELMAN--
OH! UHH!
WHO WOULD RECOMMEND
A DRUG TO JESUS
IF SHE COULDN'T
GET HIM TO SIT STILL
FOR 5 MINUTES.
NEVER FIGURED MAYBE
IT WAS HER TACTICS
AND NOT THE KID,
BUT WHATEVER.
HIS FOLKS WOULD
NEVER GET HIM TESTED
FOR HIS
MENTAL HEALTH.
COULDN'T AFFORD
THE MEDICAL BILLS.
HALF THESE DAMN KIDS
ARE SUFFERING FROM
MENTAL ILLNESS.
THAT'S THE REAL
PROBLEM HERE.
THE CLASSROOM
CAN'T FIX THAT ...
AND NEITHER CAN
RITALIN.
BUT WHAT DO THEY KNOW?
NOTHING, THAT'S WHAT.
I KNOW WHAT THESE
KIDS NEED, BUT
WHO LISTENS TO ME?
ANYWAY, WHAT THE HELL
WAS I TALKING ABOUT?
LOUIE--
LOUIE GASPACHO.
EXACTLY. SO, HE COULD
BE A REAL TERROR
IF HE WAS HAVING A DAY.
SO, ONE TIME HE
THREW A BOOK AT ME.
NEARLY KNOCKED OUT
THE SMART LITTLE
WEST INDIAN GIRL
THAT SAT...
I DON'T THINK YOU
SHOULD CALL HER THAT.
I GRABBED HIS
LITTLE SCRAWNY ASS
IN THE MIDDLE OF CLASS.
[SLAPS TABLE]
GAVE HIM 3 LICKS
TO HIS BACKSIDE.
NEVER A BOOK
THROWN AGAIN.
THAT KID GOT ALMOST
STRAIGHT As
THAT YEAR.
BUT THEY DON'T
GIVE ME MY CREDIT
FOR THAT
BECAUSE HE WAS
INSTITUTIONALIZED
A COUPLE YEARS
LATER AND--
PULLED OUT
OF SCHOOL,
SO IT WAS LIKE
HE NEVER EXISTED,
BUT I HAD HIM
FUNCTIONING HIGH,
YOU KNOW.
A GOOD OLD
ASS WHIPPING
CAN TEACH A LOT.
THAT'S NOT O's
PROBLEM, LAURIE.
OH, NO. I
WASN'T SAYING THAT.
IT'S TOO MANY THINGS.
IT'S ME. I'M THE SOURCE,
AND I KNOW IT.
AND, LOOK, I CAN'T
KEEP TALKING ABOUT THIS
IF I'M GONNA GET THROUGH
THE REST OF THE DAY, OK?
I GOTTA DRIVE UPSTATE
AFTER WORK,
PICK HIM UP.
I'LL FINISH
STRESSING THEN.
DON'T PANIC, HONEY.
WE'RE ALL A BUNCH
OF SCREW-UPS
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
OUR MESS.
YOU'LL FIGURE
IT OUT.
SCREW-UPS? REALLY?
IT'S A FIGURE
OF SPEECH.
DON'T TAKE IT LITERAL--
IT'S NOT LITERAL.
RIGHT!
OH!
LADIES.
WHAT IT DO?
WHAT IT DO
BACK TO YOU,
YOU SEXY
BASTARD.
YOU TRYING TO
GET ME IN TROUBLE
ON SCHOOL GROUNDS
AGAIN, LAURIE?
JUST A LITTLE
FLIRTATION BETWEEN
A YOUNG, HOT
SECURITY GUARD
AND A VERY AGILE,
OLD TEACHER.
IT'S HARMLESS.
FACE LOOKING GOOD, GIRL.
MM.
GOT YOU ALL BRAND-NEW.
CAN'T KEEP A WHITE
CHICK DOWN.
GLAD TO HAVE YOU BACK.
AFTERNOON, NYA.
OH, HEY, DUN.
HOW YOU DOING TODAY?
SURVIVING.
LIKE EVERY DAY.
HMM. GOOD FOR YOU.
YEP!
CAREFUL IN THE LOT
TODAY AFTER WORK.
THEY BEEN JACKING
CARS AGAIN.
THEY STILL
HAVEN'T DETERRED
THOSE BASTARDS?
NOT YET. PRINCIPAL COLDEN
SAYS WE'RE
WORKING ON GETTING
MORE SURVEILLANCE.
WHAT THE HELL'S
THE POINT OF THE
SECURITY CAMERAS
THEY PUT IN IF
IT'S NOT GONNA
SCARE OFF
THESE HOODLUMS?
I'M GONNA BE
STATIONED OUT THERE FROM
12 TO 3 P.M.
DON'T WORRY.
I WON'T LET 'EM
LAY A HAND
ON YOUR BENZ, BABY.
... YOU, FUNNY MAN.
MY ... OLDSMOBILE
HASN'T FAILED
ME YET.
IT'S LIKE HAVING
AN UGLY,
FAITHFUL HUSBAND.
NOBODY WANTS HIM
BUT ME, AND THAT'S
GOOD FOR US.
AIN'T NOTHING WRONG
WITH YOUR CAR, BABY.
GOT CHARACTER
JUST LIKE YOU.
WELL, THAT'S ENOUGH
SOCIALIZING FOR ME.
I GOTTA GET MY
CLASSROOM INTACT
BEFORE THE NEXT SET OF
HOOLIGANS COMES IN.
HEY, YOU NEED ME
TO COME UP THERE
FOR ANY REASON,
YOU KNOW HOW
TO BUZZ ME.
GOT YOU
ON PRIORITY.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
TAKE CARE OF THESE YOUNG GALS
WHO DON'T KNOW ...
ABOUT HOW TO FEND
FOR THEMSELVES.
ME, I'M AN OLD DAME.
A LITTLE RECONSTRUCTIVE SURGERY
AND I'M BACK IN THE GAME.
GOT IT, MAMA.
THIS IS MY DEN,
YOU KNOW?
THIS IS ALWAYS MY DEN.
BEEN ALL RIGHT?
YOU TALKING TO ME?
NOBODY ELSE HERE.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO THIS.
WHAT'S THAT?
MAKE SMALL TALK. CHECK ON
ME. PRETEND TO GIVE A DAMN.
REALLY. I GOT A LOT
ON MY MIND.
LOTS TO THINK ABOUT.
I DON'T NEED TO FILL
THE SPACE.
I'M COOL
WITH EMPTINESS.
GUESS YOU ARE.
WHAT?
NOTHIN'.
YOU GOT A SMOKE?
CAN'T DO THAT
IN HERE.
I'MMA TAKE IT
OUTSIDE.
DON'T WANNA HAVE
TO BUST YOU.
YOU BEING FUNNY?
WILL IT MAKE YOU SMILE?
I'M OUT OF SMILES
FOR TODAY.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
WHAT'S LEFT FOR
YOUR STUDENTS?
GWENDOLYN BROOKS.
THE POET.
YOU KNOW HER?
YOU THINK I SPEND
ALL DAY GUARDING
A SCHOOL
AND SOME OF
THE KNOWLEDGE DON'T
RUB OFF ON ME?
LOTS OF FOLKS SPEND
ALL DAY IN SCHOOL
AND DON'T LEARN DIDDLY.
IT'S VERY POSSIBLE.
TRUE DAT.
BUT I'M NOT
ONE OF THEM.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
SO, YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHY DO YOU KEEP
ASKING ME THAT QUESTION?
I WANT TO HEAR
AN ANSWER THAT
MAKES ME SATISFIED.
YEAH, I'M NOT HERE
TO SATISFY YOU.
DIDN'T SAY YOU WERE.
THEN LET IT GO.
I NEVER HEAR
FROM YOU ANYMORE.
DON'T DO THIS HERE.
THAT NEVER
HAPPENS TO ME.
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW,
THERE'S A FIRST TIME
FOR EVERYTHING.
OH, I DO SOMETHING
YOU DON'T LIKE?
YOU CAN JUST TELL ME.
DON'T GOTTA DO
THE COLD SHOULDER.
THIS ISN'T
A COLD SHOULDER.
WHAT IS IT, THEN?
IT'S SANITY. IT'S COMING
TO ONE'S SENSES.
PROFESSIONALISM.
INTELLIGENCE.
APPROPRIATE BEHAVIOR,
THAT'S WHAT THIS IS.
YOU GONNA PLAY BY
THE BOOKS ON ME?
I'M NOT PLAYING
BY THE BOOK.
JESUS, I CAN'T
DO THIS RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
DON'T DO ANYTHING.
OK.
LOOK, I GOT 10 MINUTES
BEFORE MY NEXT CLASS.
YOU SURE YOU DON'T
HAVE A SMOKE?
I REALLY NEED IT TODAY.
I NEED IT TODAY.
[TAPPING CARTON]
[CHUCKLES]
HA HA HA!
[LAUGHS]
THANKS.
THAT'S SOMETHING
WE DO WELL TOGETHER,
AIN'T IT?
WHAT'S THAT?
VICES.
I DON'T...
I GUESS...MAYBE.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
CLASS. TODAY,
WE'RE GONNA LOOK AT
ONE OF MY FAVORITE POEMS
BY GWENDOLYN BROOKS--
"WE REAL COOL.
POOL PLAYERS--
7 AT THE GOLDEN SHOVEL."
WE REAL COOL.
NOW, I WANT YOU TO LOOK
AT THIS POEM IN BOTH VERSIONS
THAT I'M SHARING WITH YOU.
NOTICE THIS LAYOUT.
WE LEFT SCHOOL.
THESE ARE FROM
TWO PUBLISHERS.
ONE, HARPERCOLLINS,
A KNOWN
WHITE AMERICAN COMPANY,
AND THE OTHER,
BROADSIDE PRESS,
ONE OF THE FIRST
MAJOR PUBLISHERS
OF BLACK
REVOLUTIONARY WRITERS.
WE LURK LATE.
REVOLUTIONARY.
COME ON, TIFFANY.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
THINK ABOUT IT.
YES. CHANGE.
THANK YOU FOR
THE ASSIST, TOMIKA.
WE STRIKE
STRAIGHT.
NOW, IN
THE HARPERCOLLINS VERSION,
LAYOUT'S PRETTY COMMON.
LARGE TITLES,
WORDS AT THE BEGINNING OF
EACH STANZA CAPITALIZED.
THERE'S ALMOST AN ATTEMPT
TO ERASE THE IDEA
THAT THE PIECE IS WRITTEN
IN BROKEN ENGLISH.
WE SING SIN.
BUT IN THE BROADSIDE PRESS
VERSION,
THE FONT LOOKS LIKE
GRAFFITI WRITING,
NOT WHAT WE NORMALLY
SEE IN OUR TEXTBOOK.
THAT'S RIGHT, DeSHAWN.
BECAUSE GRAFFITI WRITING
REPS THE 'HOOD.
AND I WOULD AGREE.
IT DOESN'T GET
THE SAME RESPECT.
WE THIN GIN.
SO, WHY DO YOU THINK
THIS INDEPENDENT BLACK PRESS
DECIDED TO LAY OUT THE POEM
IN THIS BROKEN GRAFFITI
STYLE?
WHAT ARE THEY SAYING ABOUT
RULES AND STRUCTURE?
WHAT ARE THEY SAYING
ABOUT THE EDUCATION
OF YOUNG MEN
IN THIS POEM?
WE JAZZ JUNE.
POOL PLAYERS IN THIS
POEM ARE TEENAGERS.
WHAT IF I TOLD YOU
IT WAS THE MIDDLE OF THE DAY
ON A SCHOOL DAY?
WHAT ARE THEY DOING
AT A POOL HALL
ON A SCHOOL DAY?
WE DIE.
D--D--
SO, MS. BROOKS
IS TALKING ABOUT
SOMETHING HERE.
SHE'S SAYING THEY
SKIPPING SCHOOL,
HANGING AROUND BARS,
THINNING GIN, JAZZING JUNE.
YES, DARNELL, JUNE IS
A GIRL'S NAME.
SO, "JAZZING JUNE" MEANS--
OK, PAUL, I THINK
YOU COULD COME UP
WITH A BETTER PHRASE, BUT
"LAYING THAT PIMP GAME"
WILL DO FOR NOW.
WE REAL COOL.
NOW, SOME MIGHT LOOK AT
THE BROADSIDE PRESS VERSION,
THINK IT'S INVALID
'CAUSE IT DOESN'T
FOLLOW THE RULES OF
ENGLISH GRAMMATICAL
STRUCTURE.
WE LEFT SCHOOL.
LOOKS LIKE STREET WRITING.
OMARI: WE LURK LATE.
BUT SOMETIMES RULES
ARE MEANT TO BE BROKEN.
WE STRIKE STRAIGHT.
SOMETIMES, THE STREET
HAS VALUABLE LESSONS, TOO.
WE SING SIN.
NOW, MS. BROOKS
HAS HER OWN RULES.
WE THIN GIN.
SHE BREAKS UP THE "WE"
BEFORE EACH LINE
BECAUSE SHE WANTS US
TO PAUSE.
WE...JAZZ JUNE.
SHE WANTS US TO THINK
ABOUT THAT "WE"
BEFORE THE NEXT LINE.
WE...DI--DI--DI...
EACH "WE" QUESTIONS
THEIR EXISTENCE AND WORTH.
WE...DI--DI--DI...
BECAUSE WHO ARE THEY
AT POOL HALLS?
SKIPPING SCHOOL,
DRINKING, HAVING SEX,
HANGING LATE.
WHAT WILL THEY BECOME?
WE...
GWENDOLYN BROOKS
GIVES US THE ANSWER
ON HER LAST LINE.
WE...
A LINE THAT
HAUNTS US ALL.
WE...
A LINE THAT
WILL BECOME
THEIR EPITHET.
WE...
BOTH: WE DIE...
NYA: SOON.
WHAT?
I SAID,
"WE DIE SOON."
I SEEM TO HAVE FORGOTTEN--
UH, CAN'T FIND MY PLACE--
NO, NO, I'M FINE, SHAWNA.
THANK YOU.
I THINK THAT'S
ENOUGH OF THAT--
OH, FOR TODAY.
UH, SORRY.
I'M GONNA STEP OUT.
YOU CAN WORK
SILENTLY, OK?
WORK ON YOUR OWN
RESPONSE TO THE POEM.
I'M GONNA STEP OUT.
PLEASE DON'T GET
OUT OF YOUR SEATS.
DARNELL, PAUL.
I'M SERIOUS.
THANK YOU.
[CRYING]
OHH.
DUN: YO!
HEY, HEY.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. I'M FINE.
YOU SURE?
NO. YEAH.
I'M PERFECTLY FINE.
'CAUSE IF ONE OF
THOSE LITTLE SUCKAS
IS IN THERE
CAUSING PROBLEMS,
YOU KNOW YOU JUST GOTTA
HIT ME UP, RIGHT?
I'M FINE.
I CAN HANDLE MY SON
JUST FINE.
I DON'T NEED
YOUR HELP.
YOUR SON?
WHAT? I SAID
MY STUDENT.
WHY ARE YOU--
'CAUSE YOU JUST--
LOOK, I HAVE
WORK TO DO.
HEY, YOU...
YOU OK?
I'M ... AMAZING.
OUR SCHOOL IS ...
BITCHES CAN'T NEVER MIND
THEIR OWN DAMN BUSINESS.
GOSSIP WHORES AT EVERY LEVEL.
IT'S LIKE PRIVATE SCHOOL
FOR WHAT? FOR WHO?
AIN'T NOTHING
YOU DO HERE PRIVATE.
MY PARENTS ARE STUPID CRAZY
PAYING ALL THIS MONEY
JUST TO KEEP ME
AWAY FROM THE KIDS
IN MY NEIGHBORHOOD
BECAUSE THEY'RE SO DAMN SPOOKED
I'LL END UP
GETTING PREGNANT OR SHOT
OR SOME ...
IF I GO TO PUBLIC,
BUT I'M LIKE,
THEY MUST'VE NEVER BEEN
AT THE STAIRCASE HERE
AT FRICKIN' FERNBROOK,
'CAUSE FOR REALS,
IT'S ALL TYPES OF
TEEN ... GOING ON,
AND THESE RICH BITCHES
ARE THE NASTIEST, STRAIGHT UP.
IT'S LIKE THEY PRIVILEGE
BOUGHT THEM
SOME EXTRA FREAK OR SOMETHING.
OR MAYBE THEY AIN'T NEVER KNOWN
WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE SO DESPERATE,
SO, THEY'D RATHER FIGURE THAT
OUT THROUGH SEX OR WHATEVER.
IT'S TRAGIC.
AND I CANNOT KEEP MYSELF
HERE IN THIS WASTELAND
OF TALENT.
STUCK-UP GIRLS IN MY DORM
ACTING LIKE I'M GONNA STEAL
THEIR FABRIC SOFTENER
OR GRAB THEIR GRANNY PANTIES
OUT THE LAUNDRY
'CAUSE I DON'T GOT
MY OWN OR WHATEVER.
LIKE, ARE YOU SERIOUS, BITCH?
I MAY NOT HAVE YOUR MONEY,
BUT I HAVE BOTH MY MOTHER
AND FATHER AT HOME,
WORKING THEIR ASSES OFF
AT TWO JOBS
JUST TO HAVE ME STUDY UP HERE
WITH THE REST OF YOU
BECAUSE THEY THINK
YOUR PRIVILEGE WILL
RUB OFF ON ME BY ASSOCIATION
OR SOME ... .
OR MAYBE THEY BELIEVE
IN THE FALSE GOD OF THIS
FRICKIN' FERNBROOK ACADEMY
THAT SOMEHOW
IT PRODUCES BETTER PEOPLE, BUT
I KEEP TRYING TO EXPLAIN TO THEM
THAT SOMEONE LIKE ME
WOULD ACTUALLY SURVIVE BETTER
IN AN ENVIRONMENT
IN WHICH I'M COMFORTABLE
INSTEAD OF BEING THE TOKEN
POOR GIRL OF COLOR
THAT EVERYONE THINKS IS
TRYING TO SLEEP WITH
THEIR ... BOYFRIEND
OR STEAL THEIR GODDAMN COCAINE
OR CRYSTAL METH OR WHATEVER.
MEANWHILE, THE WORST ...
MY FRIENDS ON THE BLOCK
ARE SMOKING IS WEED.
IF IT WASN'T FOR MR. PETERSON'S
SCIENCE CLASS AND OMARI,
I WOULD SLIT MY WRISTS.
THAT'S WHY I'M GOIN' AFTER O.
HE AIN'T GONNA
LEAVE ME HERE TO ROT
WITH THESE BOUGIE
BRAINWASHED BRATS.
I'M FOLLOWING MY MAN AND YOU
GONNA READ ABOUT THIS
IN ONE OF THEM
URBAN ROMANCE NOVELS.
IT'S CALLED "GHETTO LOVE."
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Y-YO, I GOT COMPANY.
LET ME CALL YOU BACK.
I GOT MORE BITCHIN' TO DO.
THAT WAS ONLY HALF.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
JASMINE.
HI.
CAN WE TALK?
OK.
I CAME UP
TO GET OMARI.
I FIGURED THAT.
HE'S SUPPOSED
TO BE HERE WITH
HIS THINGS,
MEET ME DOWNSTAIRS,
BUT HE'S NOT THERE.
NOT IN HIS ROOM.
NOWHERE.
REALLY?
YOU KNOW WHERE
HE MIGHT BE?
SORRY, MS. JOSEPH.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU SURE?
I'M SURE.
YOU SEE HIM
AT ALL TODAY?
EARLIER. I--
I SAW HIM EARLIER.
DID HE SEEM UPSET?
WAS HE HIMSELF?
DID YOU NOTICE--
I KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED.
I MEAN,
I WASN'T THERE,
I DIDN'T ACTUALLY
SEE HIM PUT HIS
HANDS ON--
BUT I WAS INFORMED.
I WAS IN CLASS
AT THE TIME
AND HE WAS
HAVING A BAD
DAY, I THINK.
A BAD DAY?
SOMETIMES, SOMEBODY
MESS WITH YOU
ON THE WRONG DAY.
IT'S LIKE THEY
DON'T KNOW IT'S
YOUR LAST STRAW.
BUT THEY AIN'T SEEN
HOW MANY TIMES
YOU BEEN SUCKED
OUTTA EVERYTHING
YOU GOT.
THEY GO PICKING
AT YOU LIKE LINT
AND THEN BE LOOKIN'
SURPRISED WHEN YOU
KNOCK 'EM FLAT
THE HELL OUT.
JASMINE.
YES?
HE'S MY ONLY SON,
YOU KNOW?
I KNOW.
I'M NOT HERE
TO HURT HIM.
I'M HERE BECAUSE
I LOVE HIM.
I WANT TO HELP MAKE
THINGS ALL RIGHT.
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
OF COURSE I DO.
SO, I NEED
YOUR HELP.
MISS, I DON'T KNOW.
OK. I HEAR THAT.
IT'S JUST THAT
YOU'RE THE PERSON
HE TALKS TO THE MOST.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
AM I?
ABSOLUTELY.
THE MOST.
AND IF ANYBODY,
IF ANYONE WOULD
KNOW HIS PLAN,
MORE THAN ANYONE ELSE
IN THE WORLD,
IT WOULD BE...
ME?
EXACTLY.
WOW. THAT'S REAL.
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE
A BIG DEAL OF THIS
TO THE SCHOOL
RIGHT NOW.
HE'S SUPPOSED
TO GET HIS THINGS,
BE WAITING
FOR ME DOWNSTAIRS.
THAT'S OUR
NORMAL ROUTINE.
HIS COUNSELOR
LEFT HIM
TO GO PACK HIS BAG,
BUT NOW NO OMARI,
AND IF I ASK
THE SCHOOL,
THEY'RE GONNA SOUND
AN ALARM,
MAKE MORE OF A PROBLEM,
AND WHATEVER TROUBLE
OMARI IS IN,
HE'LL BE FACED
WITH MORE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
GOD, MISS JOSEPH,
THEY'RE UNREASONABLE!
OK. W--WHAT DOES
THAT MEAN?
HE'S NOT A CRIMINAL.
I KNOW THAT.
I DON'T THINK HE'S
A CRIMINAL, EITHER.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW
WHERE HE IS.
SOMETIMES, PEOPLE
PUSH YOU TOO FAR.
THEY MAKE YOU FEEL LIKE
A ANIMAL
FROM ANOTHER JUNGLE,
LIKE YOU DON'T BELONG
EVEN WHEN YOU'RE HERE,
'CAUSE THEY GOT EXPECTATIONS
THAT YOU OF THE WILD.
SO, YOU BECOME
THAT EXPECTATION,
BUT IT AIN'T BORN
IN YOU, YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M SAYING?
IT'S NOT WHAT
YOU WANT TO BE.
IT'S WHAT YOU BECOME. THAT'S
THE CRAZY OF FERNBROOK.
JASMINE.
HE'S MY HEART,
MISS J. I LOVE HIM.
THEN TELL ME
WHERE HE IS.
I AIN'T NO SNITCH.
SNITCH?
I STILL COME FROM
WHAT I COME FROM.
THIS PLACE DON'T
CHANGE THAT.
JASMINE, YOU KNOW
WHERE HE WENT.
NOT EXACTLY ANYWAY.
OK, WHAT DO--WHAT
DOES THAT MEAN?
I GOT IDEAS IF I'M
IN HIS HEAD RIGHT,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
NOTHING FOR SURE.
OK, GIVE ME SOME
IDEAS HERE.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
DON'T ASK ME.
PLEASE, MISS.
I'M NOT
HIS BETRAYER.
BETRAY--WHOO--
OOH, JASMINE.
TRYING TO BE CALM.
I'M TRYING NOT TO
UNRAVEL, UNLEASH.
I DON'T WANT TO
SEE YOU UNLEASH.
THIS ISN'T AN ACT
OF LOYALTY, NOT FOR REAL.
IN YOUR HEAD, MAYBE,
BUT IN REALITY,
IN REALITY, YOU'RE
SENTENCING HIM TO AN--
I NEED TO FIND HIM.
YOU LOOK REAL
STRESSED, MISS.
OK, I'M VERY STRESSED.
HE'S MY SON.
I UNDERSTAND.
I KNOW WHAT IT FEELS
LIKE TO LOVE HIM
HARD, BELIEVE ME.
DO YOU?
HIS UNPREDICTABILITY
IS MANIC.
IT'S EXCRUCIATING
SOMETIMES,
LIKE NAILS GOING STRAIGHT
THROUGH THE HEART MUSCLE,
BUT INSIDE YOU KNOW
HE'S LIKE AN INFANT
NEEDING SOME KIND
OF NURTURE,
AND THERE'S A SWEETNESS
TO HIM THAT MAKES
YOU WANT TO GIVE IT.
IT MAKES YOU WANT TO
GIVE UP EVERYTHING JUST
TO HOLD HIM TIGHT.
JASMINE, THIS ISN'T HELPING.
DID YOU EVER
LIKE ME, MISS?
WHAT?
WHEN I'D COME OVER,
YOU HARDLY EVER REALLY--
IT'S LIKE YOU WAS
POLITE BUT NOT NICE.
I KNOW THE DIFFERENCE.
I DON'T SEE WHAT
THIS HAS TO DO
WITH FINDING--
I'M NOT TRYING TO
GRILL YOU OR NOTHING.
I JUST WAS ALWAYS CURIOUS.
LIKE IT WAS SOMETHING WRONG
I DID I DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT--
SAT IN YOUR FAVORITE
CHAIR ONCE,
DRANK THE LAST OF SOME JUICE
I DIDN'T KNOW WAS NEAR EMPTY.
LIKE IF IT WAS SOME
ACTION OF MINE
OR JUST MY PRESENCE ALONE.
I'D UNDERSTAND EITHER WAY,
JUST ALWAYS WONDERED.
JASMINE.
I DON'T DISLIKE YOU.
YEAH.
BUT YOU DON'T LIKE ME,
EITHER, RIGHT?
I MEAN, I DON'T DISLIKE YOU.
THAT'S LIKE
PASSIVE-AGGRESSIVE, SORT OF.
IT'S NOT COMMITTING
TO LOVING OR HATING.
IT'S ALMOST WORSE,
LIKE INDIFFERENT.
IT'S HARD TO LIKE
SOMEONE...
SOMEONE YOU DON'T KNOW
BEYOND A FEW HELLOS.
SOMEONE SMART
AND CUTE MOST DAYS.
STILL SOMEONE
YOU DON'T KNOW.
SOMEONE WITH A HEART SO BIG,
THE SKY COULDN'T HOLD IT.
SOMEONE WHO I'M SURE IS
GREAT IN HER OWN WAY.
SOMEONE DEFINITELY GREAT
IN EVERY WAY.
OK.
SURE.
BUT SOMEONE ALSO
DATING YOUR SON.
MY ONLY SON.
EXACTLY.
LIKE THE WAY YOU
JUST SAID THAT.
I MEAN, THAT WAS
KIND OF LIKE...
THAT WAS ALMOST A THREAT.
UHH.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LIKE...
AND, EXCUSE MY LANGUAGE,
PLEASE, BUT IT WAS LIKE,
"YEAH, BITCH, THAT'S
MY ONLY SON,
AND YOU'RE TRYING TO TAKE HIM
FROM ME OR WHATEVER."
I SAID, "EXCUSE
MY LANGUAGE, PLEASE."
I HOPE YOU HEARD THAT PART.
YEAH, I HEARD THAT PART.
HEARD IT.
AHEM.
JASMINE, DO YOU HAVE
ANY BROTHERS OR SISTERS?
THIS LIKE
A BONDING QUESTION
OR INTERROGATION
QUESTION?
WHATEVER KIND
GETS AN ANSWER.
I'M AN ONLY CHILD LIKE O.
WE CONNECT THAT WAY.
I SEE.
BUT I GOT AN OLDER COUSIN
AND ONE YOUNGER, BOTH BOYS.
THEY'RE LIKE BROTHERS
TO ME SOMETIMES.
YOU KNOW WHAT IT'S
LIKE TO TAKE CARE
OF THEM AS A WOMAN,
WORRYING ABOUT WHAT
CAN HAPPEN TO THEM
WHEN THEY GO OUT INTO
THE WORLD EVERY DAY?
UM, THEY JUST
MY COUSINS, SO--
IT'S A GAMBLE,
JASMINE, ALL THE TIME.
YOU SEND YOUR YOUNG MAN
OUT INTO THE WORLD
FOR A DAY,
AWAY FOR A WEEKEND,
A SEMESTER,
A SCHOOL YEAR,
AND YOU HAVE NO IDEA,
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
IF THEY'RE SAFE.
IF SOMEONE WILL TRY
TO EXPIRE THEM
BECAUSE THEY'RE
TOO YOUNG OR TOO BLACK
OR TOO THREATENING,
TOO LOUD, TOO UNINFORMED,
TOO ANGRY, TOO QUIET,
TOO EVERYDAY, TOO COOL,
TOO UNCOMPOSED,
TOO MYSTERIOUS,
OR JUST TOO TOO.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA,
AND IT'S FRIGHTENING,
JASMINE.
IT SENDS A TREMBLE
THROUGH YOUR HEART
ON THE DAILY.
BUT IF SOMEONE COULD
EASE THAT TREMBLE
BY UNVEILING JUST
A LITTLE PIECE OF
THE PUZZLE,
IT WOULD MEAN EVERYTHING.
DO YOU GET ME?
MEN ARE A PUZZLE,
STRAIGHT UP. I GET YOU.
SO I KNOW YOU WANT
TO PROTECT OMARI.
I KNOW YOU CARE
FOR HIM DEEPLY.
SO DEEP I GOT
INDIGESTION OVER HERE.
BUT KEEPING HIS
WHEREABOUTS A SECRET,
THAT'S NOT HELPING
HIM, YOU HEAR ME?
NOT EVEN A LITTLE BIT.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
DO IF YOU KNOW?
GO FOLLOW HIM,
CONVINCE HIM NOT TO
DO SOMETHING HE SET
HIS MIND TO?
YOU REALLY THINK
THAT'S POSSIBLE?
I WOULDN'T BE WORTH
MY SALT AS A MOTHER
IF I DIDN'T.
MS. JOSEPH,
I KNOW YOU THINK
MAYBE I'M NOT GOOD
ENOUGH FOR YOUR SON.
MY PARENTS THINK NOBODY'S
GOOD ENOUGH FOR ME.
I GET IT. NOBODY'S
GOOD ENOUGH FOR NOBODY.
BUT ME AND O, WE GOT
SOMETHING REAL.
AND EVEN IF YOU THINK
I'M WORTHLESS, I'M
STILL GONNA LOVE HIM.
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE WORTH--
NAH, YOU DO.
YOU DON'T WANT TO,
BUT YOU DO.
I CAN SMELL WHEN I DON'T
MAKE SENSE TO SOMEBODY.
I MAKE YOU AFRAID
JUST LIKE O MAKES
MY PARENTS AFRAID.
IT'S LIKE YOU SEND US
HERE TO BECOME THESE
DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
YOU WANT US
TO HAVE SO MUCH.
YOU WANT TO PROTECT
US FROM OURSELVES.
YOU LOVE US,
AND WE KNOW THAT,
BUT YOU HATE US, TOO.
YOU HATE US HAVING
A MIND OF OUR OWN.
YOU HATE THAT WE CAN'T
BE EXACTLY WHAT YOU
IMAGINED IN YOUR HEAD,
AND THAT SCARES YOU,
THAT WE DON'T
BELONG TO YOU,
THAT SOMEONE
COULD COME ALONG
AND WE MIGHT LOVE THEM
MORE THAN WE LOVE YOU.
YOU HATE US FOR THAT.
WE CAN FEEL IT INSIDE,
AND IT'LL MAKE US LEAVE
AND NEVER COME BACK!
WHERE IS...
MY SON?
JASMINE.
MAYBE THE TRAIN STATION
OR THE BUS.
TO GO WHERE?
HE DIDN'T SAY.
BUT HE SAID IT
WAS GOOD-BYE.
DID SOMEONE COME
AND PICK HIM UP?
HE CAUGHT A RIDE
WITH BRIAN.
HE TOLD THE COUNSELOR
HE WAS COMING UP TO
PACK UP HIS CLOTHES.
THEY LET HIM GO, AND HE
SNUCK OUT WITH BRIAN.
I TRIED TO CONVINCE
HIM NOT TO GO,
STICK OUT HIS FATE
LIKE A MAN,
BUT HE DIDN'T WANT TO BE
A BURDEN NO MORE TO YOU.
WHY WOULD HE BE A--
THEY VIDEOED HIM, MISS.
IT'S GONNA GO VIRAL.
SOMEBODY ALREADY
SENT ME A TEXT.
JESUS.
HE THOUGHT HE'D BRING YOU
SO MUCH SHAME.
HE THOUGHT HE'D RUIN YOU.
DID HE MENTION A PLACE?
I NEED TO KNOW NOW.
I NEED TO KNOW.
I'M TELLING YOU
EVERYTHING I KNOW.
BETRAYAL ALL DAY.
THINK FOR A MINUTE.
I NEED TO KNOW
BEFORE I LEAVE.
DID HE MENTION
ANY OTHER PLACE?
I TOLD YOU WHAT
I KNOW FOR SURE.
YOU GOING HOME EARLY
FOR THE WEEKEND, JASMINE?
UM--
DO NOT ... ME.
YOU PLANNING ON
MEETING HIM SOMEWHERE.
I WAS PLANNING
ON SEARCHING.
SEARCHING WHERE?
THE TRAIN STATION, THE BUS.
I SWEAR, THAT'S IT.
I DON'T HAVE NOTHING ELSE.
HE KEPT SAYING HE HAD
TO DO THIS ON HIS OWN,
HE HAD MONEY FROM HIS
FATHER, CHILD SUPPORT STASH.
HE SAID HE'D BE OK.
HAS HE CALLED
OR TEXTED YOU?
NO. I WISH, BUT NO.
OK, LISTEN TO ME.
LISTEN.
IF HE CALLS, TEXTS,
GETS ONLINE,
DOES ANYTHING TO
REACH YOU, YOU CALL
ME IMMEDIATELY.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
HE WON'T, MISS.
YOU'RE CUT OUT,
AND SO AM I.
JUST DO WHAT I SAY!
[MUSIC PLAYING]
MAN: ♪ GIVING UP ♪
♪ IS HARD TO DO ♪
♪ WHEN YOU REALLY ♪
♪ LOVE SOMEONE ♪
♪ GIVING UP ♪
♪ SO HARD TO DO ♪
♪ WHEN YOU ♪
♪ STILL DEPEND UPON ♪
♪ HER WARM AND TENDER TOUCH ♪
♪ HER KISS
AND HER CARESS ♪
♪ OOH ♪
♪ THAT USED TO MEAN SO MUCH ♪
♪ AND BRING YOU HAPPINESS ♪
♪ WHOA ♪
♪ GIVING UP ♪
I'M BACK, MA.
I SEE.
I, UM--
WHERE YOU BEEN?
WITH SOME FRIENDS.
FRIENDS?
JUST TRYING TO CATCH
A BUS OVER TO PHILLY.
PHILLY?
WHAT--PHILLY?
MY BOY RASHAD GOT
A SMALL CRIB THERE
FROM WHEN HIS FATHER PASSED.
SAID HE HAD A COUCH.
SO THAT'S THE PLAN, HUH--
RUN OFF AND NOT FACE
ANY OF THIS?
LEAVE ME HERE TO DEAL
WITH THE MESS. THAT'S
THE PLAN?
IT WAS SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT A PLAN.
SO WHAT HAPPENED,
YOUR PLAN GO AWRY?
NO, I JUST...
I DON'T KNOW, MA.
I JUST CAME BACK.
[SIGHS]
I SEE.
YOU BEEN SMOKING.
AND YOU BEEN FIGHTING.
I...
YOU WANT TO HEAR,
OR DO YOU EVEN CARE?
DON'T DO THAT, OMARI.
DO WHAT?
ASK IF I CARE.
DEFLECT, PUT THIS ON ME.
THAT'S NOT GONNA
FLOAT RIGHT NOW.
I'M NOT TRYING
TO DEFLECT, MA.
I'M ASKING IF YOU CARE TO HEAR
OR IF YOU PREFER NOT TO HEAR,
'CAUSE MAYBE THE DETAILS
WON'T MAKE IT BETTER RIGHT NOW.
I ALWAYS CARE.
I'M NOT SAYING YOU DON'T.
THEN, YES, TELL ME
THE GORY DETAILS,
TELL ME WHAT DEVIL
GOT INTO YOUR HANDS,
MADE YOU ATTACK
YOUR TEACHER.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND, MA.
MAKE ME.
I WANT TO START BY SAYING
I'M NOT JUSTIFYING.
THERE'S NO WAY TO...
I'M NOT JUSTIFYING,
BUT EVERYTHING I SAY NOW
IS JUST THE HOW, YOU KNOW,
THE HOW AND WHY,
BUT NOT THE EXCUSE.
I'M NOT MAKING NONE
OF THOSE NO MORE. I'M DONE.
GIVE ME THE HOW.
COULDN'T SEE STRAIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT I KNOW FOR SURE.
IT'S LIKE I WENT BLIND
FOR A SECOND,
NO INSIGHT, NO OUTER.
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO GET THROUGH THE WEEK.
WHAT BLINDED YOU, OMARI?
HE KEPT QUESTIONING ME
IN CLASS.
QUESTIONING YOU HOW?
DIDN'T FEEL LIKE
BEING BOTHERED.
I SAID THAT TO HIM, MA.
I TOLD HIM I WASN'T IN THE
MOOD FOR BEING QUESTIONED.
OMARI, HE'S YOUR TEACHER.
HE HAS THE RIGHT
TO QUESTION YOU.
NAH, HE DON'T,
NOT HOW HE WAS DOING.
BEEN DOING IT A LOT,
AND I WAS SICK OF IT.
WE GET TO DISCUSSING
THE READING,
"NATIVE SON,"
RICHARD WRIGHT,
AND HE START
ASKING QUESTIONS.
WHAT MADE BIGGER THOMAS
KILL THAT WOMAN?
WHAT WERE
HIS SOCIAL LIMITATIONS?
WHAT MADE THE ANIMAL
IN HIM EXPLODE?
AND WHO HE LOOKING AT
WHEN HE ASKING ALL
THESE QUESTIONS, MA?
WHO HE LOOKING AT?
OMARI--
LIKE I'M THE SPOKESPERSON,
LIKE I'M BIGGER THOMAS,
LIKE I'M PREDISPOSED
TO SOME ... TO KNOWING
WHAT IT'S LIKE TO BE
AN ANIMAL.
OMARI, WATCH YOUR MOUTH.
YOU HEAR ME, THOUGH?
YOU HEAR WHAT HE DOING?
HE START PICKING ME OUT,
ASKING ME TO ANSWER.
WHAT DID I DISCOVER
WHEN READING THE TEXT?
HE'S YOUR TEACHER.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO ASK YOU
ABOUT THE TEXT, OMARI.
NAH, HE AIN'T.
HE AIN'T JUST QUESTIONING
ME ABOUT "NATIVE SON."
HE AIN'T JUST TALKING TEXT.
HE'S SAYING SOMETHING ELSE,
SOMETHING BENEATH
THE QUESTION,
AND IT'S LIKE I'M THE ONLY
ONE WHO CAN HEAR IT.
THAT DOESN'T
GIVE YOU THE RIGHT
TO LOSE YOUR COOL.
THAT DOESN'T GIVE YOU
THE RIGHT TO BE
THE ANIMAL HERE.
BUT IT'S ALL HE'S SEEING.
WON'T LEAVE ME ALONE.
I SAID, "MISTER, DON'T
PICK ON ME TODAY.
I AIN'T GOT NOTHING
TO OFFER," BUT HE WON'T
LEAVE ME ALONE.
A TEACHER'S SUPPOSED
TO ENGAGE YOU,
EVEN WHEN YOU DON'T
FEEL LIKE IT.
THAT'S THE TEACHER'S JOB.
NOW, I TOLD YOU THAT
REPEATEDLY, OMARI.
WE'RE NOT TALKING THE
TEACHER DOING THEIR JOB.
WE TALKING PROVOKING.
WE TALKING AGITATING.
WE TALKING
SINGLING ME OUT.
YOU KNOW THAT, MA?
ON A DAY WHERE...
WHERE I DON'T FEEL LIKE
BEING SINGLED OUT.
WE TALKING RESPECTING
MY SPACE.
NO.
NO, YOU IN SCHOOL.
YOU'RE NOT IN YOUR
PERSONAL SPACE.
YOU'RE IN A COLLECTIVE
SPACE, A SPACE TO ENGAGE,
TO BE QUESTIONED,
TO BE STIMULATED,
TO BE PROVOKED.
THAT'S EDUCATION, OMARI.
I'M TALKING BIASED
EDUCATION, MA.
I'M TALKING DISRESPECT.
HE KNOWS.
HE KNOWS
HE WAS--
HE WAS
SAYING SOMETHING.
ASKING ME IN
THAT ROOM IN THAT WAY
IN FRONT OF ALL THOSE
STUDENTS ON THAT ISSUE,
HE WAS SAYING SOMETHING
DIRECTLY TO ME.
I KNOW HE WAS.
EVEN IF HE WAS, EVEN IF,
WHAT YOU TELLING ME?
YOU TELLING ME THAT MAKE
YOU ATTACK YOUR TEACHER?
YOU TRYING TO DRAW
SOME PERPENDICULAR LINE HERE,
'CAUSE I'M NOT SEEING
WHERE THESE THINGS CROSS.
I TOLD HIM TO BACK OFF.
YEAH, YOU SAID THAT ALREADY.
I TOLD HIM, MA,
AND HE KEPT DIGGING.
AND THEN?
AND THEN HE SAYS,
"MR. JOSEPH,
"YOUR PERSPECTIVE
IS MANDATORY HERE.
TELL THE CLASS YOUR
PERSPECTIVE OR TAKE
A ZERO FOR THE DAY."
STILL NOT SEEING.
YOU THREATEN MY GRADES,
YOU THREATEN TO PUNISH
ME IN FRONT OF THE CLASS
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO
BE YOUR TOKEN RESPONDER.
THAT'S ...
YOU CUSSING LIKE THAT?
YOU SAVING THAT DISRESPECT
FOR ME PERSONALLY.
I'M SORRY, JUST AMPED,
MAKING A POINT.
NO, BUT YOU HAVEN'T
MADE A POINT YET, OMARI.
YOU HAVEN'T GIVEN ANY
INDICATION WHY YOUR
BEHAVIOR WAS WARRANTED.
YOU HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING
EXCEPT SPEAK AS IF
YOU'RE ABOVE REPROACH.
AND YOU'RE NOT.
FORGET IT, MA.
NO.
LET'S NOT FORGET IT.
NO, LET'S.
I KNEW YOU WOULDN'T.
I KNEW THIS WAS FUTILE.
THIS IS YOUR
THIRD STRIKE, OMARI.
THE WORST ONE.
YOU PUT YOUR HANDS
ON YOUR TEACHER.
YOU ATTACK YOUR TEACHER?
I PUSHED HIM.
I DIDN'T ATTACK HIM.
YOU THINK THEY CARE
ABOUT YOUR SEMANTICS?
I PUSHED HIM AND HE FELL
AGAINST THE BOARD.
YOU SLAMMED A TEACHER
AGAINST A BOARD.
NOW THAT'S SOME SEMANTICS.
IT WAS RECORDED
BY OTHER STUDENTS,
AND NOBODY'S GONNA SEE
ANYTHING DIFFERENTLY.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
I TRIED TO GET UP AND LEAVE.
HE WOULDN'T LET ME LEAVE.
THAT'S UNREASONABLE.
I TOLD HIM I WASN'T
IN THE MOOD, MA. I TOLD HIM.
THEY DON'T CARE
ABOUT YOUR MOODS.
EXACTLY.
THEY DON'T CARE, MA.
THEY DON'T CARE WHAT
SPACE AND PLACE I'M IN.
I KNOW ME.
I KNOW HOW TO LEARN.
I KNOW WHEN I'M GOOD
AND WHEN I'M NOT,
AND I SAID IT.
"I'M NOT GOOD."
I SAID THAT.
THEN YOU ASK FOR
PERMISSION TO BE EXCUSED.
YOU SAY, "HEY! MM.
I NEED TO SPEAK TO MY
COUNSELOR IMMEDIATELY."
YOU DON'T WALK OUT IN
THE MIDDLE OF A LESSON
LIKE YOU SOME KING OR GOD
THAT NO ONE CAN TAME.
TAME?
DAMN IT, OMARI.
DON'T DO THAT.
DON'T--DON'T...
TWIST AND REMODEL THE CONVO
AND CHANGE MY MEANING.
I'M NOT CHANGING ANYTHING.
I'M REPEATING VERBATIM.
SO WHY ARE YOU HERE?
HUH?
WHAT'D YOU COME BACK
HERE FOR?
HAD NOWHERE ELSE TO GO?
I JUST...
AIN'T WANT TO LEAVE
THAT WAY.
SO WHAT'S THIS?
THIS OUR GOOD-BYE?
YOU COME TO TELL ME
GOOD-BYE?
MA--
YOU DROPPING OUT?
YOU LEAVING SCHOOL?
A SCHOOL YOUR FATHER
AND I VETTED FOR YOU,
A SCHOOL THAT WAS
GONNA GIVE YOU A--
GIVE ME ALL THESE
OPPORTUNITIES,
MAKE ME A BETTER MAN
THAN I'D BE
IF I JUST WENT TO YOUR SCHOOL,
IF I JUST STAYED HERE
IN OUR NEIGHBORHOOD.
DON'T GIVE ME HIS SPEECH, MA.
THOSE IS HIS WORDS,
NOT YOURS.
YOUR FATHER THOUGHT
IT BEST IF--
BETTER THAN
STAYING WITH HIM.
"OMARI JUST AIN'T SURVIVING
IN THIS NEIGHBORHOOD.
"HE'S TOO SMART.
HE COULD BE SOMETHING, NYA,
"JUST NOT IN THIS 'HOOD.
LET'S SEND HIM UPSTATE AND
OUT OF BOTH OF OUR HAIR."
THAT'S WHAT
MY FATHER THOUGHT.
THAT'S WHERE HIS
MONEY'S GOING.
DON'T DO THAT.
DON'T SPEAK FOR HIM.
OR ME OR US.
DON'T INTERPRET.
YOU LOST IN TRANSLATION.
I'M NOT LOST.
YOU ARE.
[SCOFFS]
[SIGHS]
[LIGHTER FLICKS]
GOING TO KILL YOURSELF
WITH THESE.
YOU CELEBRATING
MY DISAPPEARANCE?
OMARI.
NOT FUNNY, I KNOW,
BUT IT'S LIKE...
LIKE A HOMEGOING
OR SOMETHING UP IN HERE.
I AIN'T DIE, MA.
SORRY.
WE SHOULD, UM...
GET FOOD OR SOMETHING,
RIGHT?
I'M STARVED AND--
I'LL COOK US SOME PASTA.
WHAT DID I DO?
TELL ME.
MA, DON'T DO THIS.
I NEED TO KNOW
IF I HURT YOU,
IF I MISSTEPPED,
I FORGOT TOO MUCH,
I DIDN'T KNOW ENOUGH.
MA, THIS AIN'T YOU.
'CAUSE I'VE TRIED,
LIKE RELIGIOUSLY,
LIKE AN ONGOING PRAYER,
TO PROTECT YOU,
BUFFER YOU FROM IT ALL,
FLEE YOU, FREE YOU,
FOLLOW INSTRUCTIONS
FROM YOUR FATHER,
FROM OTHER MOTHERS,
FROM MY OWN MOTHER,
FROM WHOMEVER.
[SIGHS]
I STILL DON'T--
I STILL DON'T HAVE
THE ANSWER.
WHAT YOU WANT ME
TO SAY?
THEY COULD PRESS CHARGES.
WHAT YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
TAKE YOU AWAY FROM ME.
I WOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO STOP THEM.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU WANT ME TO SAY.
I DON'T--I DON'T
KNOW WHAT--
I WANT INSTRUCTIONS.
I WOULD TAKE
A BULLET FOR YOU.
I WOULD SUFFOCATE THE SUN
FOR YOU.
I WOULD STEAL
THE SKY FOR YOU.
I WOULD BLIND MOSES FOR YOU.
I WOULD STRIP THE WIND,
THE RAIN,
THE FORESTS FOR YOU.
BEFORE YOU DIE OR ROT
OR LOSE YOUR FREEDOM,
I WOULD SURRENDER MY OWN.
YOU KNOW THAT?
I WOULD DIE
IF YOU COULD BE BORN AGAIN
WITHOUT THIS
OPPRESSIVE RAGE.
I JU--I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
I NEED YOU TO TELL ME.
TELL ME HOW TO SAVE YOU.
TELL ME
HOW TO GIVE YOU
ANOTHER LIFE.
TELL ME WHAT WOULD TAKE
THIS FAILURE AWAY.
'CAUSE I LISTEN TO
EVERYBODY ELSE.
I'M READY TO LISTEN TO YOU.
GUIDE ME.
GIVE ME THE ANSWER.
GIVE IT TO ME.
I WILL DO IT, I SWEAR.
MA.
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M HUNGRY.
GONNA COOK US SOMETHING.
YOU GONNA EAT?
NO, I'M GONNA SIT HERE...
WAIT FOR INSTRUCTIONS.
[STIFLED SOBBING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
OMARI: WE REAL COOL.
WE LEFT SCHOOL.
WE LURK LATE.
WE STRIKE STRAIGHT.
WE...
WE STRIKE, STRIKE, STRIKE,
STRIKE!
WOMAN OVER P.A.:
MS. JOSEPH, PLEASE CALL
THE MAIN OFFICE.
YOU HAVE A VISITOR.
THANK YOU.
HEY, HASSELHOFF,
IT'S JOSEPH.
YEAH.
HE IS?
SHOOT.
WOULD YOU SEND HIM
UP, PLEASE?
THANK YOU.
IT'S RIGHT HERE. OK.
[MUTTERS]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[CLEARS THROAT]
COME IN.
HI, NYA.
HI, XAVIER.
[LAUGHS]
SORRY TO STOP BY
DURING SCHOOL HOURS.
THEY SAID THIS IS
YOUR FREE PERIOD.
YEAH.
JUST GOT YOUR MESSAGE
THIS MORNING.
LOST MY PHONE YESTERDAY.
HAD A MILLION CLIENTS
TO TRACK DOWN.
MARKETING ACCOUNTS
WENT CRAZY.
IT'S FINE.
I JUST TOOK HALF A DAY,
LEFT THE FIRM AND CAME
STRAIGHT DOWN HERE.
OH, OK.
CAN WE TALK ABOUT
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YEAH, SURE. OK.
HE HIT A TEACHER?
PUSHED HIM AGAINST
THE SMARTBOARD.
JESUS. WHY?
UM, I'M NOT SURE.
HE SAID HE WAS
HAVING A BAD DAY.
A BAD DAY?
SAID HE WAS, UM,
BEING HARASSED BY
THE TEACHER MORE THAN
THE OTHER STUDENTS,
SAID HE FELT TARGETED,
WASN'T IN THE MOOD
FOR ANY OF IT.
WELL, THAT'S NO EXCUSE.
I TOLD HIM THAT.
WHERE IS HE NOW?
HOME, I THINK. HOME.
YOU THINK?
[SIGHS]
I LEFT HIM AT HOME.
HE'S BEEN SUSPENDED.
THEY'RE GOING TO DELIBERATE,
DECIDE WHETHER TO EXPEL HIM,
AND PRESS CHARGES.
AND THAT'S WHERE WE ARE.
I'M LETTING IT COOL
OVER THE WEEKEND.
I'M HOPING SOME OF
THE STEAM WILL BLOW OFF,
THEY'LL BE MORE LENIENT.
WELL, THIS IS
HIS THIRD STRIKE.
YEAH, IT IS.
THEY'RE NOT GONNA
BE LENIENT
WITH A THIRD STRIKE.
WELL, I'M HOPING.
HE SAID HE DIDN'T
SLAM THAT TEACHER,
BUT ON THE VIDEO,
IT LOOKS LIKE HE PUSHED--
THE VIDEO?
YEAH.
THERE'S A VIDEO?
THE KIDS' PHONES.
HOW DID THEY--
I THOUGHT PHONES
WEREN'T EVEN ALLOWED.
THEY'RE NOT.
THEN HOW THE--
THEY'RE GONNA USE
THIS AGAINST HIM.
HE WANTED TO RUN AWAY.
HE TRIED TO RUN AWAY.
AND THIS ALL HAPPENED
YESTERDAY?
I TRIED TO CALL.
MY PHONE.
YEAH. HA HA!
DID I GIVE YOU
SHEILA'S NUMBER?
I DON'T RECALL GETTING
SHEILA'S...NUMBER.
WELL, I'LL GIVE YOU
HER NUMBER.
NEXT TIME YOU CAN'T
REACH ME, CALL HER.
SHE'LL REACH ME.
YEAH, OK.
DAMN, O.
HOW'D IT GET TO THIS?
HOW'D IT GET SO FAR
OVER THE LINE?
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, DID HE SAY
ANYTHING TO YOU,
GIVE YOU ANY ANSWERS?
[LAUGHING]
SOMETHING FUNNY?
YOU THINK HE
GIVES ME ANSWERS?
HA HA HA!
I'M JUST ASKING.
HE OUGHT TO.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO
ANSWER TO YOU.
HE'S YOUR SON.
HE'S YOUR SON, TOO.
WELL, I KNOW THAT.
WHAT...
WHAT WAS THAT?
WHAT WAS WHAT?
THAT JUST FELT A BIT
LIKE ACCUSATION.
NO, I DIDN'T DO THAT.
NO?
NO.
OK.
BECAUSE WE SAID WE
WOULDN'T DO THAT.
WE'RE NOT.
CO-PARENTING.
YES, EXACTLY.
NO BLAMING.
NO ONE
IS BLAMING.
OK.
IT JUST SOUNDED LIKE--
YEAH.
YOU SAID,
"HE'S YOUR SON."
BUT MINE WASN'T AN ACCU--
BUT IT SOUNDED LIKE YOU--
I'M TALKING ABOUT HIM.
I'M SAYING HE'S THE SON,
YOU'RE HIS MOTHER.
HE SHOULD BE GIVING
ANSWERS WHEN HE'S
QUESTIONED. HE'S THE SON.
YEAH, RIGHT, OK,
BUT YOU SAID HE'S
MY SON, NOT THE SON.
I MEANT "THE SON."
OH, OK.
I'M THINKING...
I'M THINKING HE NEEDS
A CHANGE, A BIG ONE.
YEAH.
MAYBE HE SHOULD COME
STAY WITH ME.
YOU AND SHEILA?
SHEILA STILL HAS HER PLACE.
THAT'S NOT WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
YEAH, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THAT.
MAYBE THEY WON'T
PRESS CHARGES IF WE--
IF WE TELL THEM WE'RE
CHANGING HIS CIRCUMSTANCES.
I'LL PULL HIM OUT
OF FERNBROOK.
HE'LL GET ENROLLED IN
A SCHOOL IN MY NEIGHBORHOOD.
OR HE CAN GO HERE.
HERE?
YES, HERE,
WHERE I TEACH,
AND I'VE BEEN DOING SO
FOR OVER A DECADE.
NOT HERE.
THERE ARE SOME
GOOD TEACHERS HERE.
THE SCHOOL IS FAILING, NYA.
WAS FAILING.
NOT ANYMORE.
THEY DIVIDED US INTO
4 DIFFERENT SECTIONS.
WE'RE DOING MUCH BETTER.
AND THAT'S ABOUT
STUDENT ACCOUNTABILITY
AND THE SCHOOL BOARD.
THAT'S NOT
THE STAFF HERE.
NOT ALL OF US. LOOK.
THERE ARE SOME GOOD
TEACHERS HERE.
HE KNOWS THEM.
HE'LL BE COMFORTABLE.
HE'LL BE HERE
AND UNDER MY WATCH.
OH, YOU CAN'T WATCH HIM
ALL DAY.
WELL, NEITHER CAN YOU.
BUT I CAN GIVE HIM
A BETTER SURROUNDING.
BETTER?
DON'T DO THAT.
I'M NOT MAKING JUDGMENTS.
LET'S NOT MAKE IT ABOUT THAT.
LET'S KEEP IT ABOUT O.
IT IS ABOUT O.
NOW, YOU DO WHAT YOU CAN.
I KNOW THAT.
I'M NOT SUGGESTING YOU'VE
DONE ANYTHING WRONG.
BUT YOU RESIST, YOU
AND HIM, THE OFFERS I MAKE.
NOW I'M NOT--
YOU COULD BE PROUD.
YOU COULD RIDE OR DIE
FOR THIS NEIGHBORHOOD
ALL YOU WANT.
THAT'S GOOD FOR YOU,
BUT THAT'S NOT GOOD
FOR OUR SON.
AND YOU KNOW--
YOU KNOW WHAT'S BEST?
SENDING HIM AWAY
TO FERNBROOK
DIDN'T STOP
THE RAGE.
YOU CAN'T SOLVE HIM
FROM THE OUTSIDE IN.
DON'T YOU SEE THAT?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN,
OUTSIDE IN?
I'M WORKING WITH
THE PARTS I GET, NYA.
THAT'S ALL I GET
ACCESS TO.
HE DOESN'T LET ME IN.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN I'M
NOT STILL ACTIVE.
I WORK FROM WHATEVER
WAY HE DICTATES.
HE ALWAYS DICTATES,
BUT HE'S THE SON.
OUR SON.
AND HE CAN'T ALWAYS
BE THE DICTATOR.
IT CAN'T ALWAYS BE
A DEMOCRACY.
SOMETIMES--
AND I TRY, BUT YOU,
IT'S LIKE WE'RE
RUNNING TWO DIFFERENT
GOVERNMENTS.
I THOUGHT IT WAS
CO-PARENTING.
SOMETIMES IT'S--
AND I'M NOT SAYING
YOU DON'T DO--
YOU'RE NOT RUNNING
YOUR PART,
BUT I'M THE MAN, NOT YOU,
AND HE NEEDS A FIRMER HAND.
THAT ISN'T BLAME?
MAYBE NOT ALWAYS HAVE
A CHOICE IN THE MATTER.
MAYBE HE HAS
TOO MANY DAMN CHOICES
AND DOESN'T KNOW HOW
TO FOLLOW A LEADER.
HE THINKS IT'S HIM,
BUT WHERE IS HE GOING?
AND YOU DON'T THINK
A FIRMER HAND WON'T
MAKE HIM SUFFOCATE?
YOU THINK I'M TOO LOOSE, SO
HE'S SLIPPING DOWN THE PIPE?
WELL, WHICH GRIP IS BEST?
PLEASE SHOW ME.
YOU ALWAYS DO THIS.
DO WHAT?
MAKE THIS PERSONAL,
MAKE PARENTING OUR SON
A PERSONAL BATTLE
BETWEEN YOU AND I.
IT IS BETWEEN YOU AND I.
WE MADE HIM.
IT'S NOT YOU AND I.
IT'S YOU AND HIM,
ME AND HIM,
US AND HIM.
THAT'S THE DEAL.
YOU AND I WITHOUT HIM
DOESN'T EXIST.
OUCH.
NO.
NOT OUCH.
YOU DON'T GET
TO SAY THAT.
I DON'T GET TO BE HURT?
I CAN'T FEEL PAIN?
NO. YOU DON'T
GET TO DO THAT.
OK.
THAT'S FAIR.
IT WAS PARTLY MY FAULT.
I'M NOT LOOKING
BACKWARDS.
I DIDN'T ASK YOU TO.
YOU BROKE THIS.
NOT ME. YOU.
I'M MOVING ON, AND THAT DOESN'T
MAKE ME A BAD FATHER.
I DIDN'T SAY IT DID.
YOU ALSO DIDN'T TELL OUR SON
WHO THE REAL VILLAIN IS,
AND HE THINKS IT'S ME.
I NEVER LET HIM THINK
YOU'RE THE ENEMY.
WELL, HE THINKS IT ANYWAY.
AND NOW HE WON'T HARDLY
LISTEN TO ME,
WON'T RESPECT ME ANYMORE.
THAT'S NOT ON ME.
I NEVER--I NEVER
BAD TALK YOU.
YOU UPSET WITH ME
BECAUSE I...
THAT'S FINE.
THAT'S FAIR.
BUT YOU AND HIM AND
WHATEVER IS BROKEN,
THAT'S NOT ME.
THEN LET HIM COME.
LET HIM LIVE WITH ME.
GIVE ME THAT AUTHORITY.
I HAVEN'T ANY
TO GIVE YOU.
YOU THINK FORCING HIM
IS GONNA SAVE HIM?
DO IT.
YOU WANT TO
DICTATE, TRY IT.
YOU'LL HAVE A GREAT
REBELLION ON YOUR HANDS.
I CAN DEAL WITH REBELLION.
IT'S YOU. YOU'RE
THE BARRICADE.
WHEN YOU RESIST,
HE CAN SNIFF IT.
THEN I BECOME THE ENEMY.
I WON'T RESIST.
I'LL CALL THE SCHOOL
ON MONDAY, FIRST THING.
THAT'S WHAT I'LL DO.
PULL HIM OUT OF SCHOOL
AND ASK THEM
NOT TO PRESS CHARGES.
MAYBE THEY'LL LISTEN.
THEN HE COMES WITH ME.
THAT'S THE DEAL.
THAT'S HOW WE FIX THIS.
YOU AGREE?
HOW DID WE GET HERE?
ASK YOURSELF--
I MISS YOU.
I CAN'T, NYA.
I KNOW.
DO WE HAVE A DEAL?
HE'LL HATE US BOTH.
WELL, MAYBE JUST YOU
THIS TIME.
WELL, IF IT SAVES HIS
LIFE, I'LL BE THE DEVIL.
OK.
BUT WE WAIT
UNTIL MONDAY,
UNTIL I CAN TELL HIM,
UNTIL I CAN EFFECTIVELY
RELEASE HIM.
YOU CALL ME BEFORE YOU DO.
I WANT TO BE ON MY WAY.
I WANT HIM TO HAVE
NOWHERE TO DISAPPEAR TO.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
THIS IS A DEAL.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
DON'T TELL ME THAT ...!
THAT'S ...
YOU THINK IT'S
MY FAULT?
DON'T TELL ME YOU CAME
AS FAST AS YOU COULD.
LAURIE, THAT WASN'T ME, OK?
I DID WHAT I COULD.
I CALLED.
I ... CALLED, AND
YOU DIDN'T ANSWER.
WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED
TO DO, WAIT FOREVER,
LET THEM BUST THEIR
HEADS WIDE OPEN
ON MY WATCH?
I'M SUPPOSED TO JUST
STAND BACK AND WATCH?
YOU DIDN'T CALL
RIGHT AWAY.
YOU DIDN'T.
THAT'S WHAT THE KIDS
ARE SAYING.
LAURIE: ... WHAT
THE KIDS ARE SAYING.
ASK ANY TEACHER
OVER HERE.
ASK NYA. SHE'LL TELL
YOU IT'S ...
YOU TWO ALL RIGHT?
DO I LOOK ALL RIGHT?
LAURIE'S FIFTH PERIOD,
DeSHAWN AND HAKEEM
GOT INTO A FIGHT.
NO? AGAIN?
YOU HEAR THAT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO DO ABOUT THAT?
SHE SAID "AGAIN."
THAT MEANS THESE TWO
HAVE AN ONGOING BEEF.
IT'S LIKE THE ...
CRIPS AND THE BLOODS
IN MY CLASSROOM.
THESE KIDS ARE AT WAR.
YOU WANT ME TO JUST
WATCH THEM DROP GRENADES
AND PRETEND LIKE THAT
... ISN'T LETHAL?
I DIDN'T MAKE UP
THE POLICY.
NOT PROTECT THE CIVILIANS?
NYA: DID COLDEN GIVE
YOU ... ABOUT IT?
DID COLDEN GIVE ME
... ABOUT IT?
UNDERSTATEMENT
OF THE YEAR.
NO, I CAN TALK TO HIM.
THOSE TWO HAVE BEEN AT IT
IN MY ROOM, TOO.
THAT'S NOT GONNA HELP.
WHY'S IT NOT GONNA HELP?
BECAUSE THEY'RE GONNA
THROW ME TO THE ... WOLVES.
THAT'S WHY.
BECAUSE YOU
BROKE PROTOCOL.
THERE IS NOT
PROTOCOL IN WAR.
THERE'S STOP TWO PEOPLE
FROM KILLING EACH OTHER.
THAT IS ALL.
THE BROOM?
WHAT IS IT
I SHOULD HAVE
CHOSEN INSTEAD?
PLEASE TELL ME HOW
AN OVER-THE-HILL CHICK
IS SUPPOSED TO STOP TWO
TALL TEENAGE BOYS
WITH WEIGHTLIFTING
MUSCLES AND ZERO BODY FAT
FROM POUNDING EACH
OTHER INTO OBLIVION
WITHOUT SOME
TYPE OF FORCE.
PLEASE TELL ME.
WHAT HAPPENED
WITH THE BROOM?
I HIT DeSHAWN.
SHE HIT DeSHAWN
WITH A BROOM.
TO SAVE HIS
... LIFE.
IS THAT EVEN A FACTOR?
DOES THAT EVEN MATTER?
DUN: I'M NOT SAYING
IT DO OR IT DON'T.
I'M JUST TELLING HER
WHAT WENT ...
..., LAURIE.
"..., LAURIE"?
AND COLDEN KNOWS?
OH, DeSHAWN
WENT OUT OF THE ROOM
AND STRAIGHT TO THE OFFICE.
NYA: GODDAMN.
IT'S GONNA BE
A TOUGH ONE. THAT BROOM--
WAS ALL I HAD!
WHAT HAPPENED
TO SECURITY?
WE CAME.
LAURIE: LATE.
AS FAST AS WE COULD.
HE HAD HIM
ON THE FLOOR,
BANGING HIS HEAD
INTO THE FLOOR.
DESKS WERE SCATTERING
EVERYWHERE.
KIDS WERE SCREAMING.
I CALLED SECURITY,
AND THE DAMN LINE
WAS BUSY.
WE WERE ON THE PHONE
WITH BEKIM.
HE WAS COMPLAINING
ABOUT A KID WHO WAS
HIGH IN HIS ROOM.
LAURIE: SO WHAT THE
HELL'S THE PROTOCOL
FOR BUSY SIGNAL?
WHAT AM I
SUPPOSED TO DO?
STAND ASIDE
TILL WE GET THERE.
THAT DOESN'T
ALWAYS WORK.
OF COURSE IT DOESN'T WORK.
IT'S STUPID.
I HAVE A CLASSROOM FULL OF KIDS
TO PROTECT AND MYSELF.
I MEAN, WHAT KIND OF ADULT
JUST STANDS THERE
AND WATCHES
HER STUDENTS FIGHT?
WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED
TO DO?
HE WAS POUNDING HIS HEAD
INTO THE FLOOR LIKE THIS...
LIKE HE WAS
GOING TO KILL HIM.
HAKEEM'S HEAD WAS SECONDS
AWAY FROM SPLITTING OPEN.
DeSHAWN WAS SEEING RED.
I SCREAMED TO HIM TO STOP.
DO YOU THINK
HE COULD HEAR ME?
HE COULDN'T HEAR THE VOICE
OF GOD IN THAT MOMENT.
DUN: I'M JUST SAYING
WHAT THE PROTOCOL IS.
I'M NOT SAYING
YOU WERE WRONG.
... RIGHT, AND ... WRONG!
THERE'S ONLY NECESSARY.
WHAT DID
COLDEN SAY?
OH, HE'S TALKING TO THE
PARENTS, THE SUPERINTENDENT.
NOW, ALL OF A SUDDEN,
EVERYBODY WHO DOESN'T KNOW ...
ABOUT WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO TEACH IN A CLASSROOM
IS GONNA BE MY JUDGE
AND JURY.
DO YOU WANT ME
TO DO ANYTHING?
YOU WANT ME TO TALK
TO DeSHAWN'S MOTHER?
OH, SHE'S THE LEAST
OF MY WORRIES.
... KIDS AND THEIR
CAMERA PHONES,
IS EVERYTHING A GODDAMN
YouTube SENSATION TO THEM?
THEY DIDN'T.
AND HOW THE HELL
DID THEY GET PAST SECURITY
WITH THOSE PHONES?
PLEASE TELL ME.
BACK TO ME AGAIN?
IT'S A SIMPLE
... QUESTION.
WELL, SOME STUFF GETS PAST.
IT AIN'T THE AIRPORT.
COULD'VE FOOLED ME.
WHAT'S A METAL DETECTOR
FOR IF IT DOESN'T, YOU
KNOW, CATCH ALL THE METAL?
DUN: WELL, CELL PHONES
AIN'T THE METAL WE'RE
MOST INTERESTED IN.
WHAT CAN I SAY?
DON'T SAY ... TO
ME EVER AGAIN!
LAURIE!
YOU KEEP
THINKING THIS IS ME.
YOU ACT LIKE I DID
SOMETHING WRONG.
WHAT'D I DO WRONG?
WAS I NOT ABLE TO ANSWER
YOUR CALL FAST ENOUGH?
WHEN IT'S
ONLY EIGHT OF US
WORKING 4 DIFFERENT
SCHOOLS IN ONE BUILDING,
DID I NOT REACH YOU
FAST ENOUGH?
DID I NOT RUN
FROM ONE HALLWAY
TO ANOTHER
AT A SPEED THAT MAKES
YOU SATISFIED?
I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY THAT WHEN
I'M SITTING UP HERE
BARELY BREAKING
MINIMUM WAGE AND DEALING
WITH THE ATTITUDES
OF A HUNDRED TEENS
AND TEACHERS PER MINUTE
THAT I'M NOT
A SUITABLE SERVANT
TO YOUR BECK AND CALL.
I DO WHAT I ... CAN.
I'M NOT COX
SITTING UP HERE
STEALING COMPUTERS
FROM THE SCHOOL LAB
OR BENDER FLIRTING
WITH TEENAGE GIRLS.
I'M DUN. I'M THE LAST
OF THE GOOD GUYS
WEARING A UNIFORM
AND GREETING THE KIDS
WITH A SMILE WHEN
THEY ENTER THE BUILDING.
I TRY TO MAKE A SUNNY
DAY OUT OF ...,
AND I ANSWER EVERY CALL
I GET AT THE SECURITY DESK.
I DO MY JOB, DAMN IT,
AND THIS TIME, LAURIE,
MAYBE THE JOB GOT
THE BETTER OF YOU.
THAT ... HAPPENS,
BUT DON'T GO
BRINGING ME DOWN
WITH YOU.
YOU GET IN TROUBLE,
YOU GET EARLY RETIREMENT.
YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT I GET?
I DO MY DAMN JOB.
WELL, ... THIS JOB!
I GAVE MY LIFE
TO THIS PLACE,
MY ENTIRE ... LIFE!
[EXHALES]
LOOK. SORRY.
IT'S NOT JUST LAURIE.
THESE BOYS FIGHT
ALL THE TIME,
AND I'VE TRIED EVERYTHING--
TALKING TO THEIR PARENTS,
SPLITTING THEM UP ON
OPPOSITE SIDES OF THE ROOM.
I'VE EVEN TRIED
TO STOP IT MYSELF.
WE'VE ALL TRIED.
YOU CAN'T STOP IT.
DON'T TELL ME THAT.
HOW YOU GONNA STOP IT IF
YOU DON'T KNOW THE SOURCE?
SUPPOSED TO KNOW
A MILLION AND ONE SOURCES?
YOU GOT TO KNOW WHAT
THEY CARRY IN THEM.
THE RESENTMENT
AND THE RAGE,
THERE'S A LEGACY
IN THAT.
SOURCE OF THOSE FIGHTS
IS OLDER THAN THE BRICKS
OF THIS BUILDING,
BUT NOBODY'S
DOING THEIR RESEARCH.
YOU GOT A BUNCH OF PARENTS,
TEACHERS, POLITICIANS,
WHOEVER TRYING TO
UNDERSTAND THESE KIDS.
HOW YOU GONNA UNDERSTAND
A BOOK YOU'RE ONLY SKIMMING?
NYA: HAVE TO UNDERSTAND.
MY SON'S LIFE DEPENDS ON IT.
I TRIED EVERYTHING.
YOU'RE DOING WHAT
YOU CAN, NYA.
YOU PUT HIM
IN A GOOD SCHOOL.
DOESN'T MATTER
WHERE I SEND HIM TO SCHOOL.
NOTHING IS WORKING.
HE'S BEING SUCKED
INTO THIS VOID.
TRYING TO HOLD ON TO HIM,
BUT THE FORCE IS SO STRONG,
SO MAGNIFICENT,
I HAVE TO, UH...
OMARI: STRIKE
STRIKE, STRIKE.
HOLD ON FIRM,
OR I'LL LOSE MY GRIP...
SING SIN,
SIN, SIN.
HANG ON TIGHT,
OR HE'LL START TO SLIP...
THIN GIN,
GIN, GIN.
SACRIFICE SOMETHING
MIGHTIER THAN MY SOUL.
JAZZ JUNE.
SACRIFICE SOMETHING,
WE...
SACRIFICE...
SACRIFICE,
SACRI--
DUN: NYA...
WE...
LAURIE: NYA,
ARE YOU OK?
I--
DIE!
DIE! DIE!
NO.
DIE! DIE! DIE!
AAH!
LAURIE:
ARE YOU OK?
AGH...AGH...
NYA...
SHE'S NOT
BREATHING.
NYA...
I CAN'T BREATHE.
WE DIE SOON.
LAURIE: GO! DUN,
GET THE NURSE NOW!
[SIREN APPROACHING]
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
WOMAN, ON P.A.: PAGING
DR. DAVIS. DR. DAVIS, PLEASE.
PAGING DR. DAVIS.
DR. DAVIS...
PAGING DR. ROBERTS
AT EXTENSION 278.
AT EXTENSION 278. THANK YOU.
[CLEARS THROAT]
YOU WANT SOMETHING?
I'M GOOD.
SORRY ABOUT THIS.
YEAH.
SHE'LL BE OK,
THOUGH. THEY SAID.
YEAH.
SHE'S TOUGH.
THAT'S WHAT I ALWAYS
DIG ABOUT HER.
YEAH.
PSHH. THIS NIGGA.
HEY, HOW'S SHE
HOLDING UP? ANY WORD?
[SCOFFS]
JUST HOLDING HER
FOR OBSERVATION.
I'M SORRY?
OVERNIGHT.
THEY THOUGHT IT
WAS A HEART ATTACK.
NOW THEY SAY,
LOOKS LIKE
A PANIC DISORDER,
GONNA MONITOR HER
OVERNIGHT.
I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T
REALIZE YOU WERE--
HAVE WE MET?
I'M DUN. WORK WITH HER
OVER AT THE SCHOOL,
SECURITY.
OHH, I SEE.
YOU WITH THE FAMILY?
OMARI'S MY SON.
YES. I'M FAMILY.
OH, OK.
I'M NYA'S HUSBAND--EX.
OH!
OK.
I SHOULD
LET Y'ALL--
I'LL GO DOWN TO
THE CAFETERIA.
YOU WANT
ANYTHING, O.?
I'M GOOD.
I GOT HIM.
OK.
COOL.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
I'M NOT THE ONE
IN THE HOSPITAL.
I KNOW THAT.
I JUST MEANT
WITH ALL THIS.
STUPID QUESTION.
ALL RIGHT.
PANIC DISORDER.
THAT'S
THE HYPOTHESIS.
RUNNING TESTS NOW
TO MAKE SURE
IT AIN'T DEEPER.
THANK GOD SHE'S OK.
THANK GOD.
MIGHT BE A LONG WAIT.
THE TESTS--
I'LL WAIT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEANT.
I WAS JUST
PREPARING YOU FOR--
THESE TESTS
TAKE TIME.
SHE'LL BE STRAIGHT.
I GOT HER.
I KNOW YOU DO.
SHE AND I WANTED
TO TALK WITH YOU.
WORDS AIN'T THE
MEDICINE RIGHT NOW.
STILL, I WANT
TO TALK WITH YOU,
FIND OUT ABOUT THIS
ACTING OUT IN SCHOOL.
I ALREADY PLED MY CASE,
GAVE HER THE WHOLE 1-2.
I'M SURE SHE TOLD YOU.
I WANT TO HEAR IT
FROM YOU.
FOR WHAT?
BECAUSE I DESERVE
TO KNOW.
DESERVE?
WHY IS THAT?
BECAUSE YOU PAID
FOR THE EDUCATION?
AM I WASTING
YOUR MONEY?
YOU WANT ME
TO PAY YOU BACK?
YEAH. MAYBE, SMARTASS.
MAYBE.
I'LL WRITE YOU
A CHECK.
YOU CAN CASH IT WHEN
HELL FREEZES OVER.
DON'T TALK TO ME
LIKE THAT!
I'M YOUR FATHER!
... OFF ME.
[EXHALES]
WE NEED TO WORK
THIS OUT.
I'M WORKING
MY STUFF OUT.
NAH. WITH ME.
WE NEED TO WORK
THIS OUT TOGETHER.
YOU QUIT TOGETHER
A LONG TIME AGO.
I NEVER QUIT YOU.
YOU QUIT HER,
YOU QUIT ME.
I DIDN'T--
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
THERE'S ADULT
BUSINESS THAT YOU'RE
NOT PRIVY TO.
YOU NEED TO KEEP
THE ISSUES SEPARATE.
YOU'RE MY SON.
I NEVER QUIT YOU.
SHE WAS CREEPING.
THAT'S THE ADULT BUSINESS.
THAT'S THE GROWN-UP
STUFF I CAN'T HANDLE?
NEVER MIND.
LET THIS GO.
AND YOU WERE
MEAN, COLD,
MAKING HER FEEL
LIKE ... EVERY DAY.
YOU WAS NEVER HAPPY
LIVING AROUND HERE.
THAT WASN'T HER FAULT,
MINE, NEITHER.
I TOOK GOOD CARE OF YOU,
NEVER MISSED A PAYMENT,
NEVER MISSED A BIRTHDAY
OR FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL.
YOU NEVER WENT HUNGRY,
ALWAYS HAD A SHIRT ON
YOUR BACK,
MONEY IN YOUR POCKET.
DIDN'T I DO THAT?
IS THAT MY SIN?
YOU KNOW, MOST
OF THESE DUDES
WANT THEIR OLD MAN
IN THEIR LIFE SO BAD,
THEY THINK IT'S
THE MISSING LINK
TO THE EQUATION,
A LAST INGREDIENT
TO UNDERSTANDING
THEIR MANHOOD,
BUT WHAT'S
HAVING YOU IN FLESH?
FLESH AIN'T ...
IT AIN'T NO DIFFERENT
THAN SPERM.
IT'S CLINICAL.
IT DOES THE BIOLOGY.
IT DON'T DO
THE SOUL.
THE HELL YOU
WANT ME TO DO?
YOU WANT ME TO CRY
AND ROCK YOU IN MY ARMS
TILL YOU FALL ASLEEP?
THAT'S NOT MY GIG.
I'M STILL YOUR FATHER.
I'M STILL HERE.
TITLES IS OVERRATED.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T GIVE A ...
IF YOU LIKE ME
OR YOU WANT TO GO TO THE
GODDAMN BASKETBALL COURT
WITH ME OR YOU
WANT TO PIN A ...
TAIL ON MY ASS.
I'M HERE.
I'M THE FATHER,
AND YOU'RE THE KID,
AND THAT'S THE LAW
OF THE LAND.
LIKE IT OR HATE IT--
SCREW IT--I'M HERE.
YOU AIN'T HERE.
YOU THERE.
I'M HERE.
WE MILES APART.
YOU'RE GONNA RESPECT ME.
DON'T HAVE TO LIKE ME,
DON'T HAVE TO
ENJOY MY COMPANY,
BUT THE RESPECT
IS NON-NEGOTIABLE.
OR WHAT?
YOU REALLY WANT
TO ASK ME THAT?
I WANT TO KNOW
WHAT IF I SAY NO.
SOMETIMES
I WANT TO GRAB YOU
BY YOUR THROAT AND
CHOKE THE ... OUT OF YOU.
WHAT'S STOPPING YOU?
WITNESSES.
I WAS SITTING IN CLASS
LISTENING TO THE LESSON...
WAS GONNA BE
A SILENT OBSERVER,
WAS TALKING
ABOUT "NATIVE SON."
I HAD WOKE UP THAT DAY
THINKING ABOUT YOU,
HADN'T SEEN NOR TALKED
TO YOU IN WEEKS,
BUT THE CHECK
CAME ON TIME.
I WOKE UP WITH
THAT CHECK IN MY HANDS,
AND I HAD A FEELING
ABOUT THAT,
LIKE I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY,
BUT I WANTED TO SAY
SOMETHING TO YOU.
I CALLED YOU,
BUT YOU DIDN'T ANSWER,
SO I WENT TO CLASS,
SITTING THERE LISTENING
TO THE CLASS TALK
ABOUT "NATIVE SON,"
ABOUT THE CHARACTER
BIGGER THOMAS
AND WHO HE WAS AND WHAT
LED HIM TO HIS ACT OF RAGE.
TEACHER KEPT SAYING
HE WAS UNLEASHED.
I KEPT THINKING, "ANIMAL,"
AND WE DISCUSSING
THIS BIGGER THOMAS,
DISCUSSING HIS CIRCUMSTANCES
AND WHAT HE COMES FROM
AND THIS AND THAT.
SINGLE MOTHER,
THAT GOT BROUGHT UP.
ONE OF THE STUDENTS SAID
HE ONLY HAD HIS MOTHER.
AND I'M SITTING THERE
LISTENING TO THIS
ON A DAY WHERE I WOKE UP
WITH YOU ON MY MIND
AND TRIED TO CALL YOU,
TELL YOU I HAD
THIS FEELING ABOUT
GETTING THESE CHECKS,
TELL YOU I HADN'T
SEEN YOU IN A MINUTE,
WONDER WHERE YOU BEEN,
BUT YOU DIDN'T
ANSWER YOUR PHONE,
SO I SAT THERE LISTENING
TO SINGLE-MOTHER, POOR,
ANGRY, ANIMAL
BIGGER THOMAS.
AND WHEN THE TEACHER COME
ASKING ME WHAT I THOUGHT,
I FELT LIKE HE WAS
SAYING SOMETHING TO ME,
LIKE HE KNEW I WAS
SITTING THERE THINKING
ABOUT YOU, FEELING
SINGLE-MOTHER, POOR,
ANGRY ANIMAL
BIGGER THOMAS-LIKE.
AND HE STARTS SAYING,
"MR. JOSEPH, WHAT MADE
"BIGGER THOMAS DO THAT
TO THAT GIRL?
"WHAT WERE HIS SOCIAL
LIMITATIONS?
WHAT MADE THE ANIMAL
IN HIM EXPLODE?"
AND HE LOOKING AT ME
BUT ALSO THROUGH ME,
AND I SAY, "I DON'T
WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT,"
BECAUSE ALL I'M
THINKING ABOUT IS YOU
AND HOW I HAVEN'T TALKED
TO YOU IN WEEKS
BUT I GET THIS
CHECK ON TIME,
LIKE IT'S AUTOMATED, LIKE
THE BANK SENDS IT TO ME,
AND I WANTED TO KNOW
IF YOU EVEN MAIL IT.
LIKE, IS IT
EVEN PERSONAL,
OR IS IT JUST ROBOTIC,
ROUTINE RESPONSIBILITY?
AND I'M THINKING,
"WHO DOES THAT?
"WHAT KIND OF NIGGA
JUST SENDS CHECKS
AND CALLS THAT
FATHERHOOD?"
AND WE TALKING,
"BIGGER THOMAS THIS,"
AND, "SINGLE MOTHER THAT,"
AND LIMITATIONS
AND ANIMALS EXPLODING,
AND I SAY,
"DO NOT ... CALL ON ME.
I DO NOT HAVE THE ANSWER,"
NO, AND HE KEEP
PUSHING ME AND PUSHING ME,
AND I STAND UP TO WALK OUT
BECAUSE I FEEL THE ROOM
GETTING SMALLER AND I'M
BECOMING BIGGER THOMAS,
EVEN WHEN I HATE
THIS PART OF THE STORY,
AND TEACHER GET IN MY WAY,
TELLS ME TO SIT DOWN,
GRABS ME LIKE YOU
GRABBED MY ARM
WHEN YOU TRY TO PLAY
DADDY ALL OF A SUDDEN,
AND I PUSHED THAT BITCH,
THREW HIS ASS OFF OF ME
AND INTO THE ...
SMARTBOARD,
THREW HIM LIKE HE WAS
A MONKEY HANGING ON MY BACK,
LIKE HE WAS YOU,
AND I'M WISHING
IT WAS YOU.
I'M WISHING I COULD
THROW HIM AGAIN,
POUND HIS ... FACE
INTO THE GROUND,
RIP THAT CHECK UP,
AND SAY, "VOID,"
BUT IT WASN'T YOU.
IT WASN'T YOU I PUSHED--
IT WAS MY TEACHER--
BUT I WISHED IT WAS YOU.
NO, I WISHED IT WAS YOU
SO BAD, I HAD TO PEE.
ALMOST ... PEED ON MYSELF
RIGHT THERE
IN FRONT OF THE CLASS.
AND I DON'T KNOW IF THAT
IS HATE OR LOVE
OR SOMETHING ELSE
I WAS FEELING,
BUT I KNOW WHY BIGGER THOMAS
DID WHAT HE DID,
AND I HATE THAT I KNOW,
BUT YOU I HATE MORE.
YOU I HATE MOST OF ALL.
YOU KNOW, SON, I--
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
WHEN THE DOCTOR
COMES OUT, TEXT ME.
I'M STEPPING OUT--
NEED SOME AIR--AND OFF.
I'M STEPPING OFF.
I NEED SOME AIR
FROM ALL THIS.
YOU DON'T WANT ME IN
YOUR LIFE, AND I DON'T--
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO DO ABOUT THAT.
I JUST WISH--
BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO DO.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I WAS GONNA LEAVE YOU
THIS LONG-ASS MESSAGE,
BUT I'M NOT SURE
YOU'LL EVEN GET IT.
THEN IF YOU DO,
I'M NOT SURE
YOU'LL EVEN RESPOND BACK.
I THINK IT'S OVER, AND IT
KILLS ME IN A THOUSAND WAYS,
NOT BECAUSE I'LL NEVER
FIND LOVE AGAIN--
I KNOW I'M YOUNG;
I KNOW I'M CUTE,
AND I'LL FIND SOMEBODY ELSE;
THERE'S A LOT OF FISH IN
THE SWIMMING POOL, WHATEVER--
BUT I'M JUST SAD THAT THIS
IS THE END OF AN ERA
AND IT'S OVER
BEFORE IT REALLY BEGAN.
I DON'T THINK I GOT
ENOUGH CHANCES TO ... UP
AND GET MAD AT YOU AND YELL
AND THEN MAKE UP.
I HATE THAT.
EVERY RELATIONSHIP
DESERVES TO GO
THROUGH ALL THE COLORS
OF THE RAINBOW.
THAT'S HOW YOU KNOW
YOU HAD SOMETHING--
DEEP, UGLY, BEAUTIFUL. WHATEVER.
WE DIDN'T GET TO GIVE
ALL OUR ... A TRY,
BUT FOR THE LITTLE PARTS
WE DID HAVE,
FOR THE PARTS THAT MADE ME
WANT TO CUT A CHICK'S FACE
FOR YOU TURNING YOUR HEAD
IN HER DIRECTION,
I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR GIVING ME THAT SPACE,
FOR MAKING ME FEEL ROOM ENOUGH
TO BE JEALOUS
AND MAD OR WHATEVER
BECAUSE I ALSO GOT TO SMACK YOU
AND GET IT OUT,
AND THAT MADE ME FREE ENOUGH
TO TELL YOU THAT I LOVE YOU.
I JUST REALLY, REALLY LOVE YOU,
AND I HATE YOU
FOR LEAVING ME HERE
AND BREAKING IT OFF
AND NOT KNOWING YOURSELF.
I REALLY HATE YOU FOR BEING
SO BEAUTIFUL AND CONFUSED...
AND I'M GLAD YOU'RE NOT
COMING BACK HERE ANYMORE
BECAUSE THIS PLACE
CAN'T HOLD YOU.
THIS PLACE CAN'T HOLD
NONE OF US, FOR REAL,
AND I GUESS I KIND OF DID
LEAVE YOU A LONG-ASS MESSAGE,
ANYWAY, BUT ..., YOU KNOW?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
WOMAN, ON P.A.: TODAY, STUDENTS,
WE HAVE A SPECIAL POEM
BEING READ BY OUR
ORATORY SPEECH WINNER--
CAROLINA VALDEZ.
GO AHEAD, CAROLINA.
CAROLINA, ON P.A.: "WE REAL
COOL," BY GWENDOLYN BROOKS.
NYA: I ALMOST LOST IT.
I ALMOST BROKE DOWN AND STAYED
SOMEWHERE IN THE BETWEEN.
NERVOUS BREAKDOWNS,
WHAT MOST FOLKS CALL IT.
DOCTORS CALL IT
A PANIC DISORDER.
I CALL IT MY MOMENT
OF REVELATION.
I'M SORRY, MA.
ALL MY SON'S LIFE, I THOUGHT
THERE WAS SPACE FOR HIM--
A LITTLE EDUCATION,
OPPORTUNITY,
HE'D BE COMPLETE.
BUT, MEMBERS OF THE BOARD,
I'M HERE TO TELL YOU
THAT I MISCALCULATED.
OMARI'S ACTIONS
AREN'T HIS BAG ALONE.
THEY'RE MINE,
ALL OF OURS.
WE DIDN'T CARVE OUT
ENOUGH SPACE.
HE DOESN'T BELONG ANYWHERE.
THERE'S NO BLOCK, NO SCHOOL,
NO LAND HE CAN TRAVEL WITHOUT
BEING UNDER SUSPICION AND DOUBT,
NO EMOTION HE CAN CARRY
WITHOUT BEING SILENCED,
DISCIPLINED.
HE NEEDED MORE SPACE TO BE.
CAROLINA, ON P.A.:
"WE REAL COOL, WE..."
I MESSED UP, MA.
CAROLINA, ON P.A.:
"LEFT SCHOOL. WE..."
I THINK THERE'S
SOMETHING WRONG WITH ME,
AND I AIN'T SURE
WHAT IT IS.
I WANT
HIM TO BELONG.
I WANT TO TURN
MYSELF IN, MA.
I WANT TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
I WANT TO MAKE
YOU STOP SMOKING
AND DRINKING
AND CRYING.
NO. THAT'S NOT
YOUR--
CAROLINA, ON P.A.:
"SING SIN..."
I WANT MY SON TO
HAVE ANOTHER CHANCE
TO BE BORN AGAIN
WITH A SLATE CLEAN
OF THE BAGGAGE,
OUR BAGGAGE...
CAROLINA, ON P.A.:
"JAZZ JUNE."
MY BAGGAGE.
I WANT
TO BE BETTER.
SOMETIMES I LOOK
INTO HIS FACE,
I GET STUCK STARING
AS IF I CAN SEE
WHAT HE WILL BECOME,
AND THE LONGER I LOOK,
THE LONGER
HIS LIFE WILL BE,
AND I'LL WANT HIM TO
FIND SPACE FOR HIS ANGER
WHERE HE ISN'T QUELLED
BUT PUT TO GOOD USE,
WHERE HE ISN'T
A PRODUCT OF BIAS
OR LOW EXPECTATION...
CAROLINA, ON P.A.:
"SING SIN. WE..."
AND I WANT HIM
TO KNOW LOVE...
THEY SEE ME
AS A MONSTER.
TO FEEL LOVE FROM
ALL THE PLACES.
ONLINE,
I'M A MONSTER.
PEOPLE MADE COMMENTS,
SAY I SHOULD BE
KICKED OUT,
LOCKED UP...
HE'S A MAN, YOUNG,
STILL GROWING,
NOT FULLY ANYTHING.
LIKE I'M
AN ANIMAL...
HE'S NOT AN ANIMAL.
LIKE THEY EXPECT
I WOULD BE.
YOU'RE NOT AN ANIMAL,
NO MORE THAN
THE REST OF US,
AND IF SO,
WE BUILT THE JUNGLE.
I DISAPPOINT YOU.
I CAN DO BETTER.
SO IF YOU PLEASE,
LET ME TAKE HIM
FROM HERE,
FIND A DIFFERENT
SCHOOL,
RESET, TRY AGAIN,
BUT PLEASE DON'T--
DON'T PRESS CHARGES.
DON'T LOCK AWAY WHAT
HOPES HE CAN BECOME.
HIS RAGE IS NOT HIS SIN.
IT WAS NEVER HIS SIN.
IT'S HIS INHERITANCE...
I KNOW I CAN
DO BETTER.
AND I'M HERE
BEFORE YOU TO SAY THAT
I TAKE THE BLAME.
IT'S ME. SEND ME AWAY--
PUNISH ME--BUT MY SON--
NOT MY SON...
CAROLINA, ON P.A.:
"WE DIE SOON."
NOT MY SON.
I'VE BEEN THINKING, MA,
ABOUT INSTRUCTIONS,
ABOUT WHAT YOU SAID.
YEAH?
I WROTE THEM DOWN.
INSTRUCTIONS?
YEAH.
FOR ME?
FOR EVERYBODY.
LIKE A LIST?
LIKE A SCRIPTURE.
OH, WOW. I SEE.
YOU WANT TO HEAR?
I'M DYING TO HEAR.
"ONE--HEAR ME OUT.
"2--LET ME
CHILL SOMETIMES.
"3--KNOW WHEN
TO BACK OFF.
"4--KNOW WHEN TO KEEP PUSHING.
"5--LET ME HAVE
SOME SPACE.
"6--DON'T ASSUME ME
FOR THE WORST.
"7--SHOW UP
IN PERSON.
"8--BE FAIR.
"9--FORGIVE THAT
I'M NOT PERFECT.
10--"
WHAT'S 10?
I DON'T HAVE
A 10 YET.
I'M STILL
WORKING ON IT.
THESE GOOD SO FAR?
YEAH...
OH...
SO FAR.
[APPLAUSE]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
ANNOUNCER: JOIN THE CONVERSATION
ON TWITTER AT #LFLC
AND #BROADWAYonPBS.
YOU CAN ALSO FIND MORE
FROM THESE ARTISTS AT PBS.ORG.
"LIVE FROM LINCOLN CENTER"
IS MADE POSSIBLE
BY THE FAMILY
OF ROBERT WOOD JOHNSON III--
DEDICATED TO ENRICHING THE LIVES
OF ALL AMERICANS
THROUGH MEDICAL RESEARCH,
EDUCATION, AND THE ARTS--
THE ROBERT AND RENEE BELFER
FAMILY FOUNDATION,
MERCEDES T. BASS,
AND THE NATIONAL ENDOWMENT
FOR THE ARTS.
MAJOR SUPPORT FOR THIS EPISODE
IS PROVIDED
BY THE DORIS DUKE
CHARITABLE FOUNDATION.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>> HELLO, EVERYONE, AND WELCOME
TO "AMANPOUR & CO."
HERE'S WHAT'S COMING UP.
YES, IT IS SPIKE LEE, FINALLY
THE CELEBRATED DIRECTOR IS
NOMINATED FOR BEST DIRECTOR AND
BEST PICTURE FOR
"BLACKkKLANSMAN."
HE'LL JOIN ME ON SET.
>>> PLUS AN EXCITING NEW
LITERARY VOICE, LEILA SLIMANI ON
HER DEEP EXPLORATIONS OF MODERN
WOMANHOOD.
>>> AND THE SCOTTISH FIRST
MINISTER NICOLA STURGEON ON HOW
HER COUNTRY IS BEING BETRAYED BY
BREXIT AND HOW SCOTLAND WILL GO
FOR A SECOND REFERENDUM ON THEIR
OWN INDEPENDENCE.
>>> UNIWORLD IS A PROUD SPONSOR
OF "AMANPOUR & CO."
WHEN BEA TOLLMAN'S 60-YEAR
CULINARY CAREER BEGAN, SHE
DIDN'T KNOW THE RECIPES FROM HER
COOK BOOK WOULD MAKE THEIR WAY
TO HER RIVER CRUISE LINE,
UNIWORLD.
BEA'S LOCALLY INSPIRED CUISINE
IS SERVED WHILE CRUISING THROUGH
EUROPE, ASIA, INDIA, AND EGYPT
BECAUSE, ACCORDING TO BEA, TO
TRAVEL IS TO EAT.
BOOKINGS AVAILABLE THROUGH YOUR
TRAVEL ADVISER.
FOR MORE INFORMATION, VISIT
UNIWORLD.COM.
>> ADDITIONAL SUPPORT HAS BEEN
PROVIDED BY ROSALIND P. WALTER,
BERNARD AND IRENE SCHWARTZ, SUE
AND EDGAR WACHENHEIM III, THE
CHERYL AND PHILIP MILSTEIN
FAMILY, SETON MELVIN, JUDY AND
JOSH WESTON, THE JPB FOUNDATION,
AND BY CONTRIBUTIONS TO YOUR PBS
STATION FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.
THANK YOU.
>>> WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM,
EVERYONE.
I'M AMANPOUR IN LONDON.
SPIKE LEE IS EXCITED ABOUT THE
OSCARS.
NOW, YOU MIGHT NOT THINK THAT'S
NEWS, BUT ONLY THREE YEARS AGO
HE HAD JOINED JADA PINKETT SMITH
IN BOYCOTTING THE CEREMONY,
PROTESTING THE FAMOUS OSCAR SO
WHITE.
NOW THEY ARE NOT SO WHITE AND
SPIKE LEE WILL BE THERE.
[ CHEERS ]
THAT IS SPIKE AND HIS FAMILY
CELEBRATING AS THEY WATCH THE
NOMINATIONS TWO WEEKS AGO.
HE GOT SIX NODS FOR HIS
"BLACKkKLANSMAN," INCLUDING HIS
FIRST FOR BEST DIRECTOR AND BEST
PICTURE.
THE MOVIE "DO THE RIGHT THING"
WIDELY CONSIDERED LEE'S MOST
IMPORTANT WORK WAS NOT NOMINATED
IN EITHER CATEGORY.
LEE'S FILMS HAVE ALL BEEN
PROVOCATIVE, ESPECIALLY ON THE
ACURA OF RACE.
AND IT'S VERY RELEVANT THIS WEEK
AS VIRGINIA'S TOP THREE
OFFICIALS ARE EMBROILED IN A
MIND-BOGGLING SCANDAL, TWO OF
THEM OVER THE USE OF BLACKFACE.
LEE KNOWS THE ISSUE WELL BECAUSE
HIS 2000 SATIRE BAMBOOZLED
CENTERED AROUND A TV SHOW WITH
ACTORS WEARING BLACKFACE.
SO IT IS GREAT TO HAVE SPIKE LEE
HERE IN THE STUDIO TO TALK ABOUT
DIVERSITY IN HOLLYWOOD AND THE
RACISM THAT STILL PLAGUES
AMERICA.
>>> WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM.
>> SUCH A PLEASURE, IN PERSON
THIS TIME.
>> IN PERSON.
I FEEL YOUR JOY.
>> NOT NEW YORK TO LONDON.
ACROSS THE YOUR TABLE.
>> THERE'S A SIGNIFICANT CHANGE,
BUT NOW YOU'VE BEEN NOMINATED
FOR AN OSCAR.
THAT WAS YOUR REACTION.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE COOL SPIKE
LEE?
>> WELL, I WOULD LIKE TO STATE,
IF I MAY, THAT WAS A CULMINATION
OF SIX -- THE EXUBERANCE.
IT WAS BUILDING UP, ONE, TWO,
THREE, FOUR, FIVE, AND WHAT YOU
SEE, THAT WAS NUMBER SIX.
AND WENT CRAZY.
>> SO YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY
THRILLED?
>> YES, I AM.
>> I THINK THAT'S GREAT.
>> BUT ALSO I'M THRILLED FOR MY
LONGTIME EDITOR BARRY BROWN WHO
NEVER GOT NOMINATED, MY LONGTIME
MUSIC COMPOSER, TERRENCE BLAN
CHARRED.
ADAM DRIVER, NEVER NOMINATED
BEFORE.
>> YOUR STAR IN THE FILM.
IT'S TAKEN A LONG TIME, SPIKE
WHETHER
LEE.
YOU'VE BEEN DOING THESE MOVIES
FROM THE LATE '80s AND YOU'VE
NEVER BEEN NOMINATED FOR BEST
DIRECTOR.
>> RIGHT.
>> IT'S TAKEN A WHILE.
DO YOU FEEL GREAT OR IT'S ABOUT
TIME?
>> I FEEL GREAT.
I ALSO FEEL IT'S ABOUT TIME.
I WANT TO STATE IT IS APRIL
RAINS CAMPAIGN, HASHTAG OSCAR SO
WHITE COMBINED WITH SHERYL
ISAACS, TWO AFRICAN-AMERICAN
WOMEN, SHERYL BOON ISAACS.
BEHIND HASHTAG OSCARS SO WHITE,
SHE WENT TO THE BOARD AND SAID
THIS IS A BAD LOOK.
WE HAVE TO DIVERSIFY THE VOTING
MEMBERSHIP SO EVERYBODY PERSON
OF COLOR WHO'S GOT A NOMINATION
OR AN OSCAR CAN THANK THE BOTH
OF THEM.
BECAUSE THAT CHANGED EVERYTHING.
>> IT IS REMARKABLE BECAUSE WHEN
THAT HASHTAG CAMPAIGN STARTED,
OSCARS SO WHITE, YOU OBVIOUSLY
DIDN'T GO THAT YEAR.
YOU WENT TO THE KNICKS GAME.
THIS YEAR YOU WILL BE GOING.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> WE'LL JUST GET THAT STRAIGHT.
>> YEAH.
WITH FAMILY.
>> WHICH IS GREAT.
>> YEAH.
>> SHERYL BOON ISAACS, YOU
CREDIT HER THEN AND THIS
CAMPAIGN WITH ACTUALLY MOVING
THE BALL.
THIS ISN'T JUST COSMETIC.
>> HOLLYWOOD TRADITIONALLY
CONSIDERS THEMSELVES VERY
LIBERAL.
AND THAT HASHTAG, THAT WAS NOT
GOOD PUBLICITY.
IT WAS NOT GOOD FOR THE ACADEMY
OR A GOOD LOOK.
THEY KNEW IT WAS THE RIGHT THING
TO DO.
THEY HAD TO OPEN UP THE VOTING
MEMBERSHIP.
IT HAD TO BE MORE DIVERSITY.
IT HAD TO LOOK LIKE THE REST OF
AMERICA.
>> AGAIN, THERE IS A LOT OF
DIVERSITY.
IF BEAL STREET COULD TALK.
YOU HAVE "BLACK PANTHER."
>> $1.3 BILLION.
>> IT'S JUST REMARKABLE ALL THIS
TALENT THAT IS SUDDENLY GETTING
RECOGNIZED.
IS IT REAL?
>> HERE'S THE TRICKY THING.
IN ORDER FOR THIS TO CONTINUE
AND NOT BE A TREND, DIVERSITY
HAS TO GO TO THE UPPER ECHELON,
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT,
THE GATEKEEPERS.
THEY'RE THE PEOPLE THAT DECIDE
WHAT WILL MAKE IT AND WHAT WILL
NOT MAKE IT.
>> YOU MEAN THE HEADS OF
STUDIOS?
>> YES, YES.
THEY DECIDE EVERY QUARTER,
QUARTERLY MEETINGS, WHAT WE'RE
MAKING AND WHAT WE'RE NOT.
UNLESS WE'RE IN THE ROOM, IT'S
GOING TO BE IFFY.
>> LOOK, YOU'VE NOT ONLY BEEN IN
THE ROOM, BUT YOU HAVE BEEN
LEADING THE DISCUSSION AROUND
THE CONFERENCE TABLE IN THE
ROOM.
AND YOUR FILMS HAVE BEEN NOT
JUST GROUNDBREAKING, BUT THEY'VE
BEEN WAY AHEAD OF THEIR TIME.
I MEAN, EVEN IF YOU GO BACK TO
"DO THE RIGHT THING" --
>> AND NOW PEOPLE ARE LOOKING AT
BAMBOOZLED NOW BECAUSE OF WHAT'S
HAPPENING.
>> I WAS JUST GOING TO GET
THERE.
YOU BEAT ME TO IT.
>> I SHOULD NOT BE DOING YOUR
JOB.
IT'S ALL LOVE.
>> I'M GOING TO GET TO THAT BUT
LET ME FIRST ASK YOU ABOUT
"BLACKkKLANSMAN" BECAUSE THIS IS
A FILM THAT'S BEING RECOGNIZED
IN THIS WAY.
IT'S A CRAZY PROPOSITION, RIGHT?
YOU COULDN'T MAKE THIS STUFF UP,
BUT IT'S TRUE.
>> YES.
>> SO JUST QUICKLY.
>> JORDAN PEEL, MY BROTHER
CALLED ME UP OUT OF THE BLUE.
HE WANTED ME TO CONSIDER DOING A
FILM.
HE DID A SIX-WORD PITCH.
BLACK MAN INFILTRATES KU KLUX
KLAN.
>> AND YOU SAID, YOU'RE KIDDING?
>> YEAH.
I SAID THIS IS A DAVE CHAPPELLE
SKIT?
HE SAID NO, THIS IS A TRUE
STORY.
HE WROTE A BOOKS, WE HAVE A
DISCRIMINATE.
WOULD YOU BE INTERESTED?
I SAID YES
>> IT'S AN AMAZING STORY AND
IT'S SO FUNNY BECAUSE IT'S SO
UTTERLY SERIOUS.
>> YES, AND YOU ENDED WITH A AN
UTTERLY SERIOUS MESSAGE WHICH IS
WHAT HAPPENED AT
CHARLOTTESVILLE.
>> YES.
>> EVERY FILM THAT YOU MAKE, IN
FACT, HAS A DEEP SOCIAL MESSAGE.
>> NO, I MEAN.
>> AM I GETTING TOO DEEP?
>> THERE'S A VERY FUNNY
COMMERCIAL A LONG TIME AGO.
IT HURTS.
THE THING WAS, NOT EXACTLY.
>> BUT BAMBOOZLED DOES.
LET'S JUST TALK ABOUT WHAT IT
IS.
>> RIGHT.
>> THERE ARE THESE SCANDALS
ABOUT BLACKFACE, THE USE THEREOF
AMONG THE TOP ECHELON OF LEADERS
IN VIRGINIA, INCLUDING THE
GOVERNOR AND THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL.
>> VIRGINIA AT ONE TIME WAS THE
CRADLE OF CIVILIZATION.
ISN'T IT IRONIC THAT 400 YEARS
AGO THE FIRST SLAVES WERE
BROUGHT TO JAMESTOWN, VIRGINIA,
1619, 400 YEARS AGO.
SO THE IRONY IS PERPLEXING.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO PLAY A LITTLE
BIT OF THE NEWS CONFERENCE THAT
THE GOVERNOR SAID IT WASN'T HIM
IN BLACKFACE IN THE YEARBOOK,
BUT HE DID ADMIT TO DRESSING UP
WHEN HE WANTED TO IMITATE
MICHAEL JACKSON FOR A
COMPETITION, I BELIEVE.
HERE'S THE CLIP.
>> I HAD THE SHOES, I HAD A
GLOVE, AND I USED A BIT OF SHOE
POLISH TO PUT ON MY CHEEKS.
AND THE REASON I USED A LITTLE
BIT BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW IF
ANYONE HAS TRIED THAT, BUT YOU
CANNOT GET SHOE POLISH OFF.
BUT IT WAS A DANCE CONTEST.
I HAD ALWAYS LIKED MICHAEL
JACKSON.
I ACTUALLY WON THE CONTEST
BECAUSE I HAD LEARNED TO MOON
WALK.
>> ARE YOU STALE ABLE TO MOON
WALK?
MY WIFE SAYS INAPPROPRIATE
CIRCUMSTANCES
>> INAPPROPRIATE CIRCUMSTANCES.
>> HE WAS GOING TO DO IT.
HE WAS GOING TO DO THE MOONWALK.
THANK GOD HIS WIFE -- I'M
TELLING YOU.
HE HEARD A MOUTHFUL IF HE WENT
BACK HOME.
>> IT'S JUST, AGAIN, YOU
REFLECTED ON THE STATE OF
VIRGINIA AND HISTORY BUT WHAT
ABOUT YOUR FILM?
YOU DID A FILM ABOUT THIS ALL
THOSE YEARS AGO, 2000, RIGHT?
>> RIGHT.
>> IS ANYBODY LISTENING?
HOW DOES THIS STUFF HAPPEN
TODAY?
>> BECAUSE IT NEVER WENT AWAY.
IT NEVER WENT AWAY.
RACISM, RACIST IMAGERY, ALL THIS
STUFF IS INGRAINED IN THE DNA OF
THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA.
THE VERY FLAG THAT BETSY ROSS
SEWED, THAT FLAG -- IT'S SAD
BECAUSE YOU THINK THAT WE'RE
MOVING FORWARD.
HERE'S THE THING THOUGH.
I NEVER BELIEVED IN A
POST-RACIAL SOCIETY.
WHEN MY BROTHER PUT HIS HAND ON
ABRAHAM LINCOLN'S BIBLE AND TOOK
THE OATH, THERE'S SUPPOSED TO BE
A MAGICAL, MYSTICAL MOMENT,
BOOM, RACISM GONE.
I DID NOT DRINK THAT KOOL-AID.
>> YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT YOUR
BROTHER, BARACK OBAMA?
>> YES.
ALL OF A SUDDEN RACISM WOULD
EVAPORATE, DISAPPEAR, AND WE'LL
ALL BE HOLDING HANDS AND
SINGING.
>> THIS WEEK AS WELL THERE'S A
RELATED CRISIS WITH A FAMOUS
HOLLYWOOD ACTOR LIAM NEESON WHO
TALKED ABOUT A FRIEND OF HIS --
[ WHISTLING ]
>> THAT'S A LONG WHISTLE.
>> AND SHE SAID BLACK AND HE HAD
SAID, I'M GOING TO GO AND BEAT
THE BEJESUS OUT OF HIM.
AND THEN HE'S BEEN ON THE
APOLOGY TOUR.
I WOULD LIKE TO PLAY THIS CLIP
AND GET YOUR TAKE.
>> I'M NOT RACIST.
THIS WAS NEARLY 40 YEARS AGO.
>> WOULD YOU HAVE THE SAME
REACTION IF YOUR FRIEND SAID IT
WAS A WHITE MALE.
>> SHE JUST SAID IRISH OR SCOT
OR A BRIT OR A LITH WINIAN, I
KNOW I WOULD HAVE HAD THE SAME
EFFECT.
I WAS TRYING TO SHOW HONOR,
STAND UP FOR MY DEAR FRIEND.
>> WELL, IT'S A VERY UNFORTUNATE
SITUATION, BUT I'LL HAVE TO SAY
THIS.
I REALLY CAN'T COMMENT OVERALL,
BUT LET ME SAY THIS.
THERE'S A HISTORY OF WHITE WOMEN
SAYING A BLACK MAN, A BLACK
SAVAGE RAPED THEM.
IT WASN'T JUST EMMITT TILL.
THERE'S A HISTORY OF WHITE WOMEN
IN THIS COUNTRY SAYING THAT.
THE KU KLUX KLAN WAS FORMED TO
SAVE WHITE SOUTHERN WOMANHOOD.
SO I THINK WE HAVE TO TAKE THAT
IN CONTEXT TOO.
THERE'S A HISTORY BEHIND THIS,
AND A WHOLE LOT OF PEOPLE, BLACK
MEN, HAVE BEEN MURDERED,
LYNCHED, SPENT TIME IN JAIL
BECAUSE A WHITE WOMAN ACCUSED
THEM OF RAPING THEM.
AND I THINK -- I HOPE THAT LIAM,
KNOWING ABOUT THAT HISTORY.
>> WOULD YOU SEEK TO GUIDE HIM?
HE'S OBVIOUSLY IN YOUR
PROFESSION
>> THERE'S A WHOLE BUNCH OF
PUB
PUBLICISTS AROUND HIM.
IT'S PAINFUL TO SEE THAT BECAUSE
I SEE WHAT HE'S GOING THROUGH,
BUT WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IF HE
ACTED THAT OUT?
WOULD THAT PERSON END UP IN THE
HOSPITAL?
WOULD THAT PERSON HAVE BEEN
DEAD?
WOULD ANY CHARGES BE BROUGHT
AGAINST HIM?
THAT'S SOMETHING TO THINK ABOUT
TOO.
AND THEN, FOR ME, I WONDER WHERE
THAT CAME FROM WHEN HE SAYS HE'S
NOT RACIST.
BUT IN THE MOMENT, YOUR FRIEND
TELLS YOU THIS, YOU'RE GOING TO
DO DAMAGE TO THE FIRST BLACK MAN
YOU SEE?
WHERE'S THAT COME FROM?
WHERE DOES THAT COME FROM?
>> HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO SAY ON STAGE?
>> NOT YET.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO JINX
ANYTHING HERE.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
THAT'S UNJINXED.
>> IT'S A POWERFUL PLATFORM.
>> OH, YES, AND SEVERAL PEOPLE
HAVE TOLD ME, HAVE PULLED MY
COAT TAILS SAYING,
SPIKE, IF THINGS DO WORK OUT,
WITHIN THE AMOUNT OF TIME, I
ALREADY TOLD YOU HAVE 90 SECONDS
TO MAKE THAT COUNT BECAUSE I
WILL HAVE A PLATFORM, AND PEOPLE
WILL BE WATCHING AROUND THE
WORLD.
>> TALKING ABOUT WATCHING AROUND
THE WORLD, PEOPLE AROUND THE
WORLD HAVE WATCHED YOUR FILMS
SINCE YOU FIRST STARTED.
"DO THE RIGHT THING," YOU SAID,
AND YOU CONTINUE TO SAY, IS
STILL RELEVANT TODAY.
THE ISSUES
THAT YOU HIGHLIGHTED AND ZOOMED
IN ON THERE, YOU KNOW,
>> THIS COMING 30th WILL BE 30
YEARS.
>> EXACTLY, GENTRIFICATION OF
MINORITY NEIGHBORHOODS.
POLICE VIOLENCE, PARTICULARLY TO
THE CHARACTER RADIO --
>> WE WERE TALKING ABOUT GLOBAL
WARMING.
>> WHICH IS INCREDIBLE WHEN I
EVEN
THINK ABOUT THAT.
CAN I JUST PLAY A CLIP?MUS. HOT
>> YES.
>> LET ME TELL YOU THE STORY OF
RIGHT HAND, LEFT HAND.
TALE OF GOOD AND EVIL.
HATE IS WHAT THIS HAND.
LOVE, THESE FIVE FINGERS, THEY
GO STRAIGHT TO THE SOUL OF MAN.
THE RIGHT HAND, THE HAND OF
LOVE.
THE STORY OF LIFE IS THIS.
STATIC.
ONE HAND IS ALWAYS FIGHTING THE
OTHER HAND.
AND THE LEFT HAND IS KICKING MY
CHAIR.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE RIGHT HAND
LOVE IS FINISHED.
BUT HOLD ON, THE RIGHT HAND IS
COMING BACK.
SEE THAT?
HE'S GOT THE LEFT HAND ON THE
ROPES NOW, THAT'S RIGHT.
HE'S DOWN.
LEFT HAND, KO BY LOVE.
>> LOVE WON 30 YEARS AGO IN "DO
THE RIGHT THING."
>> I'M VERY SAD NOW BECAUSE THAT
DEAR FRIEND OF MINE, BILL NUN,
IS NO LONGER WITH US.
AND I DIDN'T WRITE THAT.
THAT'S FROM A SCENE FROM NIGHT
OF THE HUNTER DIRECTLY CHARLES
LAWTON HAD LOVE AND
HATE TATTOOED AN HIS FINGERS.
I SAW THAT IN FILM SCHOOL.
AND WHEN I GRADUATED FILM SCHOOL
IT MADE A BIG IMPRESSION ON ME.
AT THE TIME, THE FASHION WERE
THOSE LOVE RINGS, LET ME PUT IT
IN HERE.
ONLY MADE A FEW DIFFERENT
TWEAKS.
THAT WAS WRITTEN BY JAMES AGY.
I CANNOT TAKE CREDIT.
>> THAT IS REMARKABLE AS WELL.
I HADN'T REALIZED THAT IN THE
OLD, OLD FILM.
>> YES, BLACK AND WHITE.
>> BUT THEN IT WAS RELEVANT
THERE AND IT'S RELEVANT TODAY.
>> YES.
>> SO DOES LOVE HAVE A CHANCE
STILL OF WINNING?
>> I ALWAYS BELIEVE THAT.
BUT THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES OF AMERICA, HIS COMMENTS
ABOUT CHARLOTTESVILLE, SUPPOSED
TO BE THE LEADER OF THE FREE
WORLD.
THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA IS
SUPPOSEDLY THE CRADLE OF
DEMOCRACY.
THE PRESIDENT, I DON'T CALL HIM
BY HIS NAME, HAD A CHANCE TO
TELL AMERICA BUT ALSO THE WORLD
THAT AMERICA IS STILL ABOUT
LOVE.
HE HAD AN OPPORTUNITY,
COMMENTING ON CHARLOTTESVILLE,
TO DENOUNCE THE KLAN, TO
DENOUNCE THE ALT-RIGHT, TO
DENOUNCE THE NEO-NAZIS.
HE CHOSE NOT TO.
AND I FIND IT VERY STRANGE THAT
IN THE STATE OF THE UNION SPEECH
HE HAD SEVERAL PEOPLE, HOLOCAUST
SURVIVORS, INDIVIDUALS WHO
LANDED IN NORMANDY TO FIGHT
AGAINST THE NAZIS.
NAZIS.
CHARLOTTESVILLE, THEY HAD
SWASTIKAS.
THEY WERE DOING THE ZEEG HAIL.
THEY WERE SAYING JEWS, BLOOD,
SOIL, WHICH IS A NAZI SLOGAN.
IT DOES NOT CONNECT WITH THE
STATE OF THE UNION SPEECH AND
WHAT HE SAID AFTER
CHARLOTTESVILLE.
I MEAN, THAT'S MY OPINION.
>> HE ALSO HAD A STATE OF THE
UNION, THE LADY WHO HE HAD
RELEASED FROM JAIL, THE
AFRICAN-AMERICAN WOMAN.
WHAT DID THAT SAY TO YOU?
>> WAH WAH.
THAT DOES NOT, TO ME, DISMISS
ALL THIS STUFF.
THAT WAS POLITICS.
AGAIN, I REFER TO THE STATEMENT,
A VERY POWERFUL STATEMENT TO ME,
DEEDS, NOT WORDS.
>> I WANT TO ASK YOU ONE LAST
QUESTION BECAUSE BRINGING IT
BACK A LITTLE BIT TO MICHAEL
JACKSON AND ANOTHER ENTERTAINER.
YOU THROW A MICHAEL JACKSON
BLOCK PARTY IN BROOKLYN EVERY
YEAR.
>> FOR THE LAST NINE YEARS.
>> HE'S BEEN DEAD NEARLY TEN
YEARS NOW.
THERE'S A NEW FILM "LEAVING
NEVERLAND" THAT HIGHLIGHTS THE
STORY OF TWO MEN WHO SAY THEY
WERE ABUSED BY JACKSON AND IT
PREMIERED AT SUN DANCE LAST
MONTH.
CAN YOU SEPARATE THE ARTIST FROM
THE MAN, THE ART FROM THE MAN?
ARE YOU STILL IN THE MOOD FOR
THROWING MICHAEL JACKSON --
>> FIRST OF ALL, I HAVE NOT SEEN
THE FILM, SO I CANNOT COMMENT ON
IT.
I READ THOSE GUYS HAVE SAID
SEVERAL TIMES ON SEVERAL
OCCASIONS THAT MICHAEL DID NOT
MOLEST THEM.
SO THIS IS A VERY DIFFICULT
THING BECAUSE IT'S ALWAYS BEEN
DYNAMIC.
CAN YOU SEPARATE AN ARTIST FROM
THEIR WORK?
EXAMPLE, LENI RIEFENSTAHL, GREAT
FILMMAKER, BUT WAS SHE A NAZI?
I MEAN, IT'S DIFFICULT.
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT HITLER'S
FAVORITE FILMMAKER.
>> YES.
>> ON THAT NOTE, VERY SERIOUS
AND PROFOUND NOTE, THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NEXT TO A SMALL
NATION CAUGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF
AN ENORMOUS TUG OF WAR.
AND TO THE WOMAN LEADING THE
DEFENSE.
SHE IS NICOLA STURGEON, FIRST
MINISTER OF SCOTLAND, ONE OF A
HANDFUL OF FEMALE HEADS OF
GOVERNMENT AROUND THE WORLD.
SINCE THE U.K. VOTED FOR BREXIT
BACK IN 2016, SCOTLAND HAS BEEN
CAUGHT UP IN THIS CRISIS AGAINST
ITS WILL.
IT VOTED OVERWHELMINGLY TO STAY
IN THE EU.
NICOLA STURGEON HAS BEEN A
LEADING VOICE FOR A SECOND
REFERENDUM AND IS DOING
EVERYTHING TO MAKE SURE HER
ECONOMY SURVIVES BREXIT AND THAT
MISSION HAS BROUGHT HER TO THE
UNITED STATES WHERE BREXIT IS AN
ONGOING TOPIC OF FASCINATION AND
SOME CONFUSION.
OUR MICHEL MARTIN CAUGHT UP WITH
STURGEON IN NEW YORK.
S.
>> FIRST MINISTER, THANK YOU SO
MUCH FOR JOINING US.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
IT'S LOVELY TO BE HERE.
>> MOST AMERICANS KNOW THAT
SCOTLAND HAS A LONG AND
FRUITFUL, CLOSE RELATIONSHIP
WITH THE UNITED STATES BOTH
CULTURALLY, ECONOMICALLY AND
LOTS OF OVER WAYS -- OTHER WAYS.
I WONDER IF THERE'S SOMETHING
ABOUT THE TONE OF THE CURRENT
ADMINISTRATION THAT CONCERNS
YOU.
YOU PROBABLY HEARD SOME OF THE
PRESIDENT'S STATE OF THE UNION.
>> I DID.
>> HE TALKED ABOUT PUTTING
AMERICA'S INTERESTS FIRST AND I
WONDER IF THERE'S SOMETHING THAT
CONCERNS YOU THAT YOU NEED TO
ADDRESS WHILE YOU'RE HERE.
>> I THINK IT'S NO SECRET THAT
I'M NOT ALIGNED POLITICALLY WITH
THE CURRENT PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES.
WE DISAGREE AND DIFFER ON MANY
THINGS.
BUT AS YOU SEE, SCOTLAND AND THE
U.S. HAVE A VERY STRONG AND
LONG-STANDING RELATIONSHIP.
AND THAT RELATIONSHIP ENDURES
REGARDLESS OF WHO OCCUPIES THE
OFFICE OF PRESIDENT OR FIRST
MINISTER OF SCOTLAND.
I SUPPOSE THE TIMING OF MY VISIT
HAS MORE TO DO WITH THE
DEVELOPMENTS IN THE U.K., BREXIT
IS AN ISSUE THAT IS OCCUPYING
MUCH OF OUR THINKING.
AND I WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT THE
REST OF THE WORLD KNOWS THAT
WITHSTANDING BREXIT, SCOTLAND
WANTS TO MAKE SURE OTHER
COUNTRIES TO KNOW THEY ARE OPEN
AND WELCOMING AND THEY WANT TO
ATTRACT STROIFRTS LIVE AND WORK
IN OUR COUNTRY.
>> ONE REASON SOME AMERICANS ARE
INTERESTED IN BREXIT, APART FROM
ALL THE OBVIOUS, IS THAT THEY
SAW THIS AS A PRECURSOR TO WHAT
HAPPENED IN THE UNITED STATES
WITH THE RISE OF DONALD TRUMP AS
PRESIDENT.
WHAT IS YOUR VIEW ABOUT WHAT LED
TO BREXIT?
>> I THINK SOME OF THE FACTORS
BEHIND BREXIT ARE PROBABLY THE
SAME FACTORS THAT PERHAPS WERE
BEHIND THE ELECTION OF DONALD
TRUMP AS PRESIDENT OF THE U.S.
OBVIOUSLY THEY'RE DIFFERENT
SI
SITUATIONS, BUT THE BREXIT VOTE
IRONICALLY WASN'T ENTIRELY TO DO
WITH THE EUROPEAN UNION AND THE
U.K. MEMBERSHIP OF THE EUROPEAN
UNION.
MANY PEOPLE WHO VOTED TO LEAVE
THE EU VERY VOTING AGAINST THE
STATUS QUO BECAUSE THERE'S
UNDERSTANDING CONCERN IN THE
U.K. ABOUT RISING LEVELS OF
INEQUALITY AND POVERTY, PEOPLE
FEELING AS OF THE STATUS QUO IS
NOT SERVING THEY WILL WELL.
THAT SOMETIMES MANIFESTS ITSELF
WITH IMMIGRATION.
SOME OF THOSE SAME FACTORS
PLAYED IN THE ELECTION OF DONALD
TRUMP.
>> YOU'VE BEEN BLUNT ABOUT
SAYING THE U.K. ISN'T READY, THE
MAY GOVERNMENT IS NOT READY TO
MEET IN THIS DEADLINE.
>> THE PROOIFRMS SHOULD ASK
EUROPEAN FOR AN EXTENSION OF THE
DEADLINE.
AFTER TWO AND A HALF YEARS, SHE
AND HER GOVERNMENT HAVE BEEN
COMPLETELY INCAPABLE OF COMING
UP WITH A PLAN TO LEAVE THE EU
IN AN ORDERLY, WELL-MANAGED
FASHION.
SO THE RISK NOW IS THAT WE LEAVE
AT THE END OF MARCH WITH NO
AGREEMENT IN PLACE, AND THAT
WOULD HAVE QUITE CATASTROPHIC
EFFECTS FOR ALMOST EVERY ASPECT
OF LIFE IN THE U.K.
EVEN IF AN AGREEMENT IS STRUCK,
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME TO DO
ALL OF THE PRACTICAL THINGS TO
PUT THAT AGREEMENT INTO EFFECT.
IN MY VIEW, HOW TO LEAVE THE
EUROPEAN UNION AND THE U.K.,
THEY SHOULD PUT THEIR SHOES BACK
TO THE PEOPLE IN THE REFERENDUM.
>> IT'S MY UNDERSTANDING WE'VE
ASKED WHETHER -- IT APPEARS THAT
IT'S NOT SO MUCH THAT THERE'S
BUYER'S REMORSE, THAT PEOPLE WHO
WERE AGAINST IT ARE STILL
AGAINST IT, EVEN MORE THAN
AGAINST IT NOW.
SO WHAT WOULD ANOTHER REFERENDUM
ACCOMPLISH.
>> THERE'S TRUTH IN WHAT YOU
JUST SAID.
THE OPINION POLLS WOULD SUGGEST
THAT OPINION IS STILL EVENLY
BALANCED.
ALTHOUGH THEY WOULD ALSO SUGGEST
IF THERE WAS ANOTHER REFERENDUM,
THE OUTCOME PROBABLY WOULD BE TO
REMAIN IN THE EU.
AND I GUESS IN ANOTHER
REFERENDUM YOUNG PEOPLE WHO BY
AND LARGE WANTED TO STAY IN THE
EU MIGHT BE MORE LIKELY TO VOTE.
>> THE ARGUMENT IS THAT PEOPLE
ARE BETTER EDUCATED NOW THAN
THEY WERE BEFORE.
>> IRONICALLY.
A BIT OF BOTH.
PEOPLE ARE MORE AWARE AND OTHERS
ARE UNDOUBTEDLY MORE INFORMED
ABOUT THE DOWNSIDES.
PEOPLE HAVE SEEN THE MESS OF
BREXIT SINCE THE VOTE.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANY ROOM
FOR COMPLACENCY.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE A CASE AND YOU
HAVE TO TWWIN THAT CASE.
I
IRONICALLY PEOPLE ARE MUCH MORE
INFORMED NOW THAN THEY WERE
BEFORE THEY VOTED.
>> PEOPLE MAY REMEMBER THAT
THERE WAS A REFERENDUM ON
INDEPENDENCE AND SCOTLAND VOTED
AGAINST IT.
IT WAS A VERY SPIRITED DEBATE.
I DON'T KNOW IF CAMPAIGN WAS THE
RIGHT WORD.
>> UNLIKE THE BREXIT VOTE,
PEOPLE REALLY GOT INTO THE
ISSUES BEFORE THE VOTE.
SO PEOPLE VOTED KNOWING ALL THE
IN HIS AND OUTS AND THE PROS AND
CONS.
>> THAT'S MY UNDERSTANDING THAT
PART OF THE REASON PEOPLE VOTED
AGAINST IT WAS THEY WANTED O
STAY WITHIN THE EU.
>> IRONICALLY, IN THE
INDEPENDENCE CAMPAIGN, ONE OF
THE ARGUMENTS MADE BY THOSE WHO
WERE AGAINST INDEPENDENCE WAS IF
SCOTLAND VOTED TO BE
INDEPENDENT, WE WOULD BE VOTED
OUT OF THE EU AND WE WOULD HAVE
TO REPLY FOR MEMBERSHIP.
THAT DID SCARE SOME PEOPLE.
HERE WE ARE FOUR YEARS LATER
BECAUSE WE'RE NOT INDEPENDENT,
WE'VE BEEN TAKEN OUT OF THE
EUROPEAN UNION.
THAT UNDOUBTEDLY BRINGS THE
ISSUE OF INDEPENDENCE BACK TO
THE FORE IN MANY PEOPLE'S MINDS.
WE ARE IN THIS POSITION BECAUSE
WE'RE NOT INDEPENDENT.
62% OF PEOPLE IN SCOTLAND VOTED
TO STAY IN THE EU.
SO THAT DEMOCRATIC DEFICIT THAT
SCOTLAND FACES HAS BEEN PART OF
THE U.K. UNDOUBTEDLY MAKES MANY
PEOPLE WANT TO LOOK AGAIN AT THE
ISSUE OF SCOTLAND BECOMING AN
INDEPENDENT COUNTRY.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU?
ARE YOU LOOKING AGAIN AT THE
PROSPECT OF ANOTHER REFERENDUM
ON SCOTTISH INDEPENDENTS?
>> I THINK THERE WILL BE ANOTHER
INDEPENDENCE REFERENDUM TO BE D.
OBVIOUSLY THERE'S A LOT OF
CONCERN ABOUT THE BREXIT
PROCESS.
AS FIRST MINISTER OF SCOTLAND, I
SAID I WOULD SET OUT MY VIEW
ONCE WE SEE HOW THIS PLAYS OUT.
>> I'M PRESSING THE QUESTION
BECAUSE IT SOUNDS TO ME YOU'RE
SAYING SCOTLAND HAS HAD ENOUGH.
SO NO MATTER WHAT BRITAIN
DECIDES TO DO, SCOTLAND WANTS TO
BE INDEPENDENT NOW BECAUSE
YOU'VE SEEN THE MOST NEGATIVE
CONSEQUENCES.
>> SURE.
>> EVEN POTENTIAL CONSEQUENCES
IS ENOUGH FOR PEOPLE TO SAY
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
>> I THINK THERE WILL BE
ANOTHER -- I THINK THERE SHOULD
BE ANOTHER INDEPENDENCE
REFERENDUM.
I'M NOT YET CERTAIN OF EXACTLY
WHAT THAT SHOULD HAPPEN.
BECAUSE RIGHT NOW A FEW WEEKS
FROM BREXIT WE DON'T KNOW
WHETHER THE U.K. WILL LEAVE WITH
A DEAL OR WITHOUT A DEAL OR NOT
AT ALL.
THERE COULD BE ANOTHER GENERAL
ELECTIONS IN THE U.K. BECAUSE OF
THIS CHAOS.
SO I THINK WE NEED TO JUST WAIT
AND SEE A LITTLE BIT WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN BEFORE I COME
FOR A VIEW ON INDEPENDENCE.
>> DO YOU THINK IN THREE YEARS,
FIVE, THAT SCOTLAND WILL BE
APPLYING TO THE EU AS AN
INDEPENDENT NATION?
>> I WOULD LOVE TO THINK SO, AND
I THINK IT WILL.
I'M NOT GOING TO PUT A
PARTICULAR TIME FRAME ON IT, BUT
IN THE NOT-TOO-DISTANT FUTURE
SCOTLAND WILL BE AN INDEPENDENT
COUNTRY AND WILL LOOK TO JOIN
THE EU AS AN INDEPENDENT COUNTRY
AND TAKE A SEAT FROM THE UNITED
NATIONS.
>> I JUST WANT TO ASK ABOUT YOU.
YOU BELONGED TO THAT SMALL CLUB
OF WOMEN, HEADS OF GOVERNMENT,
THE LEGISLATIVE BODY IN THE
UNITED STATES ELECTED THE
LARGEST NUMBER OF WOMEN SERVING
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
STILL A TINY MINORITY, NOWHERE
NEAR HALF.
GENDER EQUALITY HAS BEEN AN
ISSUE FOR YOU.
YOU'LL BE AMPLIFYING THIS ISSUE
ON THE WORLD STAGE.
I WANTED TO KNOW IF YOU HAVE
SOME SORT OF CORE PRINCIPLES FOR
HOW YOU PURSUE THIS QUESTION AS
A HEAD OF STATE.
>> WHAT I WOULD SAY AND HOW I
COME AT THIS ISSUE IS SHIFTING
PEOPLE'S MIND-SET ON IT.
INSTEAD OF SEEING EFFORTS TO
SUPPORT WOMEN INTO LEADERSHIP
POSITIONS ACROSS ALL SECTION OF
SOCIETY, THE WE SHOULD ACTUALLY
LOOK AT IT FROM THE OTHER WAY
AROUND.
UNLESS YOU TAKE THE VIEW,
HOPEFULLY NOT MANY PEOPLE DO,
THAT WOMEN ARE SOMEHOW LESS
CAPABLE OF BEING IN SENIOR
POSITIONS, THEN ANY
ORGANIZATION, WHETHER IT'S
GOVERNMENT OR A COMPANY OR
PUBLIC ORGANIZATION THAT DOESN'T
HAVE GENDER DIVERSITY AND EQUAL
REPRESENTATION IS OBVIOUSLY
DOING SOMETHING WRONG BECAUSE
THERE MUST BE BAD EARS TO WOMEN
PROGRESSING AND I'M A GREAT
BELIEVER WE SHOULD ALL LEAD BY
EXAMPLE.
AS YOU SEE, TWO FEMALE HEADS OF
GOVERNMENT, I HAVE A
GENDER-BALANCED CABINET AND WE
ENCOURAGE ALL ORGANIZATIONS
ACROSS SCOTLAND TO TAKE ACTION.
AND THE OTHER THING THAT WE
REALLY NEED TO, I THINK,
ENCOURAGE UNDERSTANDING, THIS IS
NOT SOMETHING TO DO JUST BECAUSE
IT'S GOOD FOR WOMEN AND IT'S
FAIR FOR WOMEN.
ALL OF THE EVIDENCE NOW SAYS
THAT COMPANIES, ORGANIZATIONS,
GOVERNMENTS THAT HAVE GREATER
DIVERSITY AND GREATER
REPRESENTATION OF WOMEN IN THEIR
DECISION MAKING PERFORM BETTER.
SO THERE'S A REALLY HARD REASON
TO WANT GENDER EQUALITY AS WELL.
>> THERE ARE THOSE WHO HAS IT AS
SOCIAL ENGINEERING.
I KNOW THERE'S A LOT OF
RESISTANCE IN THIS COUNTRY.
>> SURELY TO HAVE A SOCIETY
WHERE WOMEN ARE SO
UNDERREPRESENTED, THAT'S SOCIAL
ENGINEERING GOING ON FOR
GENERATIONS.
WE WANT TO UTILIZE THE TALENT OF
ALL OUR POPULATION, NOT HALF.
WOMEN ARE AS CAPABLE OF BEING
GOVERNMENT LEADERS, HEADS OF
THE FACT THAT WE HAVE THIS
INEQUALITY BETWEEN THE GENDERS,
THAT'S A SIGN THAT SOMETHING IS
WRONG, IT'S NOT EFFORTS TO
ADDRESS THAT THAT ARE SOCIAL
ENGINEERING, THAT'S ABOUT WHAT
WOMEN FACE.
>> THIS IS A SENSITIVE SUBJECT
AND WEIR NOT GOING TO LITIGATE
IT HERE.
YOUR PREDECESSOR AS FIRST
MINISTER WAS ACCUSED OF VERY
SERIOUS MISCONDUCT WHEN IT COMES
TO HIS RELATIONSHIPS WITH WOMEN.
BUT YOUR ROLE IN THIS HAS BEEN
CRITICIZED.
I KNOW YOU HAD MEETINGS WITH HIM
WHILE THIS MATTER WAS BEING
INVESTIGATED.
IS THAT LEADING BY EXAMPLE?
>> I CAN'T GO INTO DETAIL
BECAUSE IT'S A CRIMINAL
PROCEEDING.
BUT WHAT I'VE ALWAYS SOUGHT TO
ACT ON AS WELL AS TALK ABOUT IS
THE FACT THAT NOBODY SHOULD BE
GIVEN SPECIAL TREATMENT BECAUSE
OF THE SENIORITY OF THE
POSITION.
WE'RE SITTING HERE TALKING ABOUT
THIS IN ITSELF AS EVIDENCE THAT
IT WASN'T SIMPLY BRUSHED UNDER
THE CARPET BECAUSE OF THE
IDENTITY OF THE PERSON INVOLVED.
AND THAT'S WHAT I THINK IS
IMPORTANT.
I CAN'T GO INTO THE DETAIL OF
ANY OF THIS BECAUSE OF THE
CIRCUMSTANCE, BUT NOBODY SHOULD
BE ABOVE ACCOUNTABILITY FOR
THESE ISSUAES.
WHEN COMPLAINTS COME FORWARD,
THEY MUST BE TREATED AND
INVESTIGATED PROPERLY.
THAT'S AN IMPORTANT PRINCIPLE I
ADVOCATE AND ALWAYS WILL.
>> DO YOU FEEL AS A WOMAN LEADER
YOURSELF, AND ONE OF THE VERY
FEW THAT YOU HAVE SOME SPECIAL
RESPONSIBILITY?
WHAT IS YOUR SPECIAL
RESPONSIBILITY WHEN IT COMES TO
THAT?
>> I THINK TO SAY SPEAK UP AND
ENSURE THAT WOMEN ARE TAKEN
SERIOUSLY AND THAT WOMEN ARE NOT
AUTOMATICALLY DISBELIEVED AND
THAT WE HAVE SYSTEMS IN PLACE
THAT ALLOW CONCERNS TO BE DEALT
WITH.
IF WE FALL SHORT ON THOSE, TO
ADDRESS THAT AND MAKE SURE WE
GET IT RIGHT IN THE FUTURE.
AS A WOMAN I FEEL STRONGLY ABOUT
THESE ISSUES, AND I FEEL A
RESPONSIBILITY ON THESE ISSUES.
BUT IT CAN'T JUST BE THE
RESPONSIBILITY OF WOMEN.
OFTEN WE TALK ABOUT THE BEHAVIOR
AND THE CONDUCT OF MEN, AND MEN
HAVE TO TAKE OWNERSHIP AND
RESPONSIBILITY FOR THAT AS WELL.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT I THINK WE
SHOULDN'T FORGET
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
SPEAKING TO US.
>>> HOW RIGHT SHE IS.
ANYONE CAN AND SHOULD HELP LIFT
UP WOMEN EVERYWHERE.
IT'S AN ISSUE CLOSE TO THE HEART
OF MY NEXT GUEST, THE FRENCH
MOROCCAN AUTHOR ALA SLIMANI,
SHE'S A CARD-CARRYING FEMINIST.
THE PERFECT NANNY, LOAN AS
LULLABY IN THE U.K. AND ADELE.
BITING LOOKS INTO THE LOT OF
WOMEN TODAY.
SLIMANI IS ONE OF 12 FEMALE
WRITERS TO WIN FRANCE'S
PRESTIGIOUS PRIZE.
SHE WRITES ABOUT FEMALE IDENTITY
AS WELL AS RACIAL AND CLASS
TENSIONS THAT TON PLAYING THE
WEST.
>> WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU WROTE TWO BOOKS THAT HAVE
GRABBED ATTENTION.
THERE'S VERY, VERY MUCH -- HOW
CAN I SAY.
YOU PUSH YOUR CHARACTERS TO THE
EXTREME.
YOU PUSH THE STORY TO THE
BUT THEY'RE ALSO BASED ON KIND
EXTREME.
OF BITS OF AUTOBIOGRAPHIES.
BUT THEY'RE ALSO BASED ON KIND
LET'S TAKE LULLABY, WHICH I
OF BITS OF AUTOBIOGRAPHIES.
THINK IN AMERICA WAS CALLED THE
LET'S TAKE LULLABY, WHICH I
PERFECT NANNY.
THINK IN AMERICA WAS CALLED THE
>> EXACTLY.
PERFECT NANNY.
>> IT IS EVERY MOTHER'S
>> EXACTLY.
NIGHTMARE OR EVERY MOTHER WHO
>> IT IS EVERY MOTHER'S
CAN AFFORD CHILD CARE THAT WANTS
NIGHTMARE OR EVERY MOTHER WHO
TO GO TO WORK.
CAN AFFORD CHILD CARE THAT WANTS
WHAT MADE YOU WANT TO TACKLE
TO GO TO WORK.
THAT PARTICULAR SUBJECT?
WHAT MADE YOU WANT TO TACKLE
>> I THINK I WANTED TO WRITE
THAT PARTICULAR SUBJECT?
ABOUT MY NIGHTMARES.
>> I THINK I WANTED TO WRITE
I WANT TO WRITE ABOUT WHAT'S
ABOUT MY NIGHTMARES.
FRIGHTENING ME THE MOST.
I WANT TO WRITE ABOUT WHAT'S
MAYBE IF I WRITE ABOUT IT, IT'S
FRIGHTENING ME THE MOST.
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN TO ME.
MAYBE IF I WRITE ABOUT IT, IT'S
I'M ABLE TO CONTROL IT.
NOT GOING TO HAPPEN TO ME.
AND CAN BE, LIKE ANY MOTHER OR
I'M ABLE TO CONTROL IT.
PARENT, AFRAID OF SOMETHING
AND CAN BE, LIKE ANY MOTHER OR
HAPPENING TO MY CHILD AND MY
PARENT, AFRAID OF SOMETHING
CHILDREN COULD DIE.
HAPPENING TO MY CHILD AND MY
IN MY FIRST BOOK, ALDELE IS
CHILDREN COULD DIE.
AFRAID OF ADDICTION.
IN MY FIRST BOOK, ALDELE IS
I HAVE THIS FEELING IF I WRITE
AFRAID OF ADDICTION.
ABOUT IT, IT'S NOT GOING TO
I HAVE THIS FEELING IF I WRITE
HAPPEN.
ABOUT IT, IT'S NOT GOING TO
>> THAT'S EXTRAORDINARY.
HAPPEN.
LET'S TAKE LULLABY FIRST, THE
>> THAT'S EXTRAORDINARY.
PERFECT NANNY.
LET'S TAKE LULLABY FIRST, THE
IT DID HAPPEN.
PERFECT NANNY.
THESE THINGS DIDN'T HAPPEN TO
IT DID HAPPEN.
YOU, BUT YOU TOOK STORIES THAT
THESE THINGS DIDN'T HAPPEN TO
WERE RAW.
YOU, BUT YOU TOOK STORIES THAT
I REMEMBER IT HAPPENED A FEW
WERE RAW.
BLOCKS FROM MY HOUSE IN
I REMEMBER IT HAPPENED A FEW
NEW YORK, A WORKING COUPLE
BLOCKS FROM MY HOUSE IN
ENTRUSTED THEIR CHILDREN TO A
NEW YORK, A WORKING COUPLE
CENTRAL AMERICAN NANNY, AND THEY
ENTRUSTED THEIR CHILDREN TO A
CAME HOME TO FIND TWO OF THEIR
CENTRAL AMERICAN NANNY, AND THEY
KIDS STABBED TO DEATH.
CAME HOME TO FIND TWO OF THEIR
AND YOU BEGIN YOUR BOOK, LULLY,
KIDS STABBED TO DEATH.
WITH THIS HORRENDOUS, HORRENDOUS
AND YOU BEGIN YOUR BOOK, LULLY,
SCENE.
WITH THIS HORRENDOUS, HORRENDOUS
I'M GOING TO READ A BIT OF IT.
SCENE.
THIS IS WHEN THEY FOUND THE
I'M GOING TO READ A BIT OF IT.
LITTLE GIRL WHO WAS STILL ALIVE
THIS IS WHEN THEY FOUND THE
WHEN THE AMBULANCES CAME.
LITTLE GIRL WHO WAS STILL ALIVE
SHE SEEMS TO BE GASPING FOR AIR.
WHEN THE AMBULANCES CAME.
HER THROAT WAS FILLED WITH
SHE SEEMS TO BE GASPING FOR AIR.
BLOOD, HER HEAD SMASHED
HER THROAT WAS FILLED WITH
VIOLENTLY AGAINST THE BLUE CHEST
BLOOD, HER HEAD SMASHED
OF DRAWERS.
VIOLENTLY AGAINST THE BLUE CHEST
IT'S VERY VIOLENT BEGINNING TO A
OF DRAWERS.
BOOK.
IT'S VERY VIOLENT BEGINNING TO A
DO YOU DO THAT ON PURPOSE.
BOOK.
>> YEAH.
DO YOU DO THAT ON PURPOSE.
I THINK I WAS NOT AWARE HOW
>> YEAH.
VIOLENT IT WAS, BUT I NEEDED TO
I THINK I WAS NOT AWARE HOW
BEGIN WITH SOMETHING VERY
VIOLENT IT WAS, BUT I NEEDED TO
VIOLENT FOR THE REWARD TO BE
BEGIN WITH SOMETHING VERY
VERY ATTENTIVE, EVERY DETAIL I
VIOLENT FOR THE REWARD TO BE
WAS GOING TO DESCRIBE AFTER
VERY ATTENTIVE, EVERY DETAIL I
BECAUSE MY STORY IS VERY
WAS GOING TO DESCRIBE AFTER
TRIVIAL.
BECAUSE MY STORY IS VERY
THIS IS THE STORY OF A NANNY AND
TRIVIAL.
TWO PARENTS AND CHILDREN.
THIS IS THE STORY OF A NANNY AND
AND THE LIFE OF A NANNY IS VERY
TWO PARENTS AND CHILDREN.
REPETITIVE.
AND THE LIFE OF A NANNY IS VERY
EVERY DAY SHE DOES THE SAME
REPETITIVE.
THING.
EVERY DAY SHE DOES THE SAME
HOW COULD I AS A WRITER GIVE TO
THING.
THE REWARD THE APPETITE TO READ
HOW COULD I AS A WRITER GIVE TO
SUCH A BOOK THAT IS GOING TO BE
THE REWARD THE APPETITE TO READ
VERY REPETITIVE?
SUCH A BOOK THAT IS GOING TO BE
SO I NEEDED TO BEGIN BE
VERY REPETITIVE?
SOMETHING VERY STRONG SO
SO I NEEDED TO BEGIN BE
FRIGHTENING MY REWARD SO THE
SOMETHING VERY STRONG SO
REWARD GOES DEEP INTO THE BOOK
FRIGHTENING MY REWARD SO THE
AND TRY TO UNDERSTAND THE WHY
REWARD GOES DEEP INTO THE BOOK
THE NANNY DID SUCH A THING
AND TRY TO UNDERSTAND THE WHY
>> I'M INTERESTED THAT YOU CHOSE
THE NANNY DID SUCH A THING
THAT PARTICULAR EPISODE.
>> I'M INTERESTED THAT YOU CHOSE
IT HAPPENED FAR AWAY FROM YOUR
THAT PARTICULAR EPISODE.
OWN EXPERIENCE IN NEW YORK.
IT HAPPENED FAR AWAY FROM YOUR
IT HAPPENED A FEW YEARS AGO.
OWN EXPERIENCE IN NEW YORK.
A FEW BLOCKS AWAY FROM FROM
IT HAPPENED A FEW YEARS AGO.
WHERE I LIVE.
A FEW BLOCKS AWAY FROM FROM
SO I REMEMBER THE AREA BEING
WHERE I LIVE.
CBEING
SO I REMEMBER THE AREA BEING
CORDONED OFF.
CBEING
AS A NANNY, SHE WAS TERRIFIED
CORDONED OFF.
LIKE YOU WERE.
AS A NANNY, SHE WAS TERRIFIED
IT WAS REALLY SHOCKING.
LIKE YOU WERE.
BUT ARE YOU SAYING ALSO
IT WAS REALLY SHOCKING.
SOMETHING ABOUT WOMEN?
BUT ARE YOU SAYING ALSO
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT MOTHERS
SOMETHING ABOUT WOMEN?
WHO NEED TO GO BACK TO WORK OR
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT MOTHERS
WHO WANT TO GO BACK TO WORK?
WHO NEED TO GO BACK TO WORK OR
AND THE RISKS OR TRADEOFFS OR --
WHO WANT TO GO BACK TO WORK?
ARE YOU SAYING SOMETHING MORE
AND THE RISKS OR TRADEOFFS OR --
THAN JUST THAT PHYSICAL DANGER?
ARE YOU SAYING SOMETHING MORE
>> NO.
THAN JUST THAT PHYSICAL DANGER?
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS THAT
>> NO.
WHEN WE HAVE IT ALL AS A WOMAN
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS THAT
WHEN WE ARE A WIFE, A MOTHER,
WHEN WE HAVE IT ALL AS A WOMAN
JOURNALIST, LAWYER, IN MY BOOK
WHEN WE ARE A WIFE, A MOTHER,
IT'S VERY DIFFICULT ACTUALLY TO
JOURNALIST, LAWYER, IN MY BOOK
HAVE IT ALL.
IT'S VERY DIFFICULT ACTUALLY TO
AND YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO SACRIFICE
HAVE IT ALL.
SOMETHING.
AND YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO SACRIFICE
IF YOU SACRIFICE TIME FOR YOUR
SOMETHING.
CHILDREN OR YOUR JOB AND YOU
IF YOU SACRIFICE TIME FOR YOUR
ALWAYS FEEL INCOMPLETE.
CHILDREN OR YOUR JOB AND YOU
AND I WANTED ALSO TO SHOW, TO
ALWAYS FEEL INCOMPLETE.
EXPRESS THAT WHEN YOU ARE AWAY
AND I WANTED ALSO TO SHOW, TO
FROM YOUR CHILDREN AND YOU GO TO
EXPRESS THAT WHEN YOU ARE AWAY
WORK AND YOU SMILE AND YOU TRY
FROM YOUR CHILDREN AND YOU GO TO
TO BE PERFECT AND TO DO YOUR JOB
WORK AND YOU SMILE AND YOU TRY
AS PERFECTLY AS YOU CAN, THE
TO BE PERFECT AND TO DO YOUR JOB
TRUTH IS THAT YOU HAVE SO MUCH
AS PERFECTLY AS YOU CAN, THE
ANXIETY AND YOU FEEL SO WORRIED
TRUTH IS THAT YOU HAVE SO MUCH
ABOUT YOUR CHILDREN, DO THEY
ANXIETY AND YOU FEEL SO WORRIED
MISS ME?
ABOUT YOUR CHILDREN, DO THEY
ARE THEY OKAY?
MISS ME?
AND YOU WOULD LIKE TO BE WITH
ARE THEY OKAY?
THEM.
AND YOU WOULD LIKE TO BE WITH
AND AT THE SAME TIME, WHEN YOU
THEM.
ARE WITH THEM, SOMETIMES YOU
AND AT THE SAME TIME, WHEN YOU
WOULD LIKE TO BE SOMEWHERE ELSE.
ARE WITH THEM, SOMETIMES YOU
SO IT'S VERY DIFFICULT TO BE A
WOULD LIKE TO BE SOMEWHERE ELSE.
WOMAN TODAY AND TO HAVE IT ALL
SO IT'S VERY DIFFICULT TO BE A
>> HONESTLY, IT IS PERPETUALLY
WOMAN TODAY AND TO HAVE IT ALL
DILEMMA.
>> HONESTLY, IT IS PERPETUALLY
THE CHARACTER IN YOUR BOOK IS OF
DILEMMA.
MOROCCAN HERITAGE.
THE CHARACTER IN YOUR BOOK IS OF
THE NANNY IS WHITE, A FLIP TO
MOROCCAN HERITAGE.
WHAT HAPPENED IN THE UNITED
THE NANNY IS WHITE, A FLIP TO
STATES.
WHAT HAPPENED IN THE UNITED
MERRIAM WAS WARY OF WOMEN WHO
STATES.
COULD BE SO CRUEL.
MERRIAM WAS WARY OF WOMEN WHO
SHE WANTED TO STRANGLE THE ONES
COULD BE SO CRUEL.
WHO PRETENDED TO ADMIRE HER OR
SHE WANTED TO STRANGLE THE ONES
ENVY HER.
WHO PRETENDED TO ADMIRE HER OR
THE STRANGERS WHO ASKED WHAT SHE
ENVY HER.
DID FOR A LIVING AND LOOKED AWAY
THE STRANGERS WHO ASKED WHAT SHE
WHEN SHE SAID SHE WAS A
DID FOR A LIVING AND LOOKED AWAY
STAY-AT-HOME MOTHER.
WHEN SHE SAID SHE WAS A
SO MANY WOMEN WILL RECOGNIZE
STAY-AT-HOME MOTHER.
THAT NO MATTER WHAT COUNTRY THEY
SO MANY WOMEN WILL RECOGNIZE
COME FROM.
THAT NO MATTER WHAT COUNTRY THEY
>> YEAH.
COME FROM.
I THINK THAT WE CAN BE VERY
>> YEAH.
CRUEL TO THE WOMAN WHO DOESN'T
I THINK THAT WE CAN BE VERY
WORK, WHO PREFERS TO STAY WITH
CRUEL TO THE WOMAN WHO DOESN'T
THEIR CHILDREN.
WORK, WHO PREFERS TO STAY WITH
WE DECESPISE HER.
THEIR CHILDREN.
I'M A FEMINIST, BUT AT THE SAME
WE DECESPISE HER.
TIME I THINK WOMEN SHOULD HAVE
I'M A FEMINIST, BUT AT THE SAME
THE CHOICE AND WE SHOULD NOT
TIME I THINK WOMEN SHOULD HAVE
JUDGE SOMEONE WHO DECIDES TO
THE CHOICE AND WE SHOULD NOT
STAY WITH THEIR CHILDREN.
JUDGE SOMEONE WHO DECIDES TO
>> THIS ALL COMES OUT AT A TIME
STAY WITH THEIR CHILDREN.
WHEN WE'RE RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
>> THIS ALL COMES OUT AT A TIME
OF ME TOO, RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
WHEN WE'RE RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
OF JUST AS BIG SOCIAL STRUGGLES
OF ME TOO, RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
FOR WOMEN TO HAVE EQUAL
OF JUST AS BIG SOCIAL STRUGGLES
OPPORTUNITY IN THE WORKPLACE,
FOR WOMEN TO HAVE EQUAL
AND CERTAINLY TO GET EQUAL PAY
OPPORTUNITY IN THE WORKPLACE,
FOR EQUAL PAY, EQUAL JOBS.
AND CERTAINLY TO GET EQUAL PAY
SO, AGAIN, IT'S REALLY A SHOCK
FOR EQUAL PAY, EQUAL JOBS.
TO THE SYSTEM THIS KIND OF STORY
SO, AGAIN, IT'S REALLY A SHOCK
AT THIS TIME.
TO THE SYSTEM THIS KIND OF STORY
>> YEAH.
AT THIS TIME.
THAT'S WHY I WANTED TO BUILD A
>> YEAH.
STORY THAT TAKE PLACE ONLY IN
THAT'S WHY I WANTED TO BUILD A
THE APARTMENT.
STORY THAT TAKE PLACE ONLY IN
I THINK THE DOMESTIC PLACE IS
THE APARTMENT.
VERY IMPORTANT.
I THINK THE DOMESTIC PLACE IS
AND WE DON'T SPEAK ABOUT IT A
VERY IMPORTANT.
LOT OR ENOUGH, I THINK.
AND WE DON'T SPEAK ABOUT IT A
I THINK THAT DOMESTIC PLACE IS A
LOT OR ENOUGH, I THINK.
POLITICAL PLACE, THE PLACE OF
I THINK THAT DOMESTIC PLACE IS A
DOMINATION, OF POWER BETWEEN
POLITICAL PLACE, THE PLACE OF
PARENT AND CHILDREN, BETWEEN MEN
DOMINATION, OF POWER BETWEEN
AND WOMEN, BETWEEN DOMESTIC AND
PARENT AND CHILDREN, BETWEEN MEN
EMPLOYEES.
AND WOMEN, BETWEEN DOMESTIC AND
AND WE HAVE TO TALK ABOUT THAT
EMPLOYEES.
BECAUSE THERE IS NO EQUALITY
AND WE HAVE TO TALK ABOUT THAT
BETWEEN MEN AND WOMEN IF WE
BECAUSE THERE IS NO EQUALITY
DON'T SHARE THE TASK INSIDE THE
BETWEEN MEN AND WOMEN IF WE
HOUSE, IF WE DON'T SHARE THE
DON'T SHARE THE TASK INSIDE THE
PARENTHOOD WITH THE CHILDREN.
HOUSE, IF WE DON'T SHARE THE
SO IT'S IMPORTANT TO SPEAK ABOUT
PARENTHOOD WITH THE CHILDREN.
THAT IN A POLITICAL WAY
SO IT'S IMPORTANT TO SPEAK ABOUT
>> I NEVER HEARD IT PUT THAT
THAT IN A POLITICAL WAY
WAY, BUT YOU ARE RIGHT.
>> I NEVER HEARD IT PUT THAT
THE DOMESTIC SPACE IS A
WAY, BUT YOU ARE RIGHT.
POLITICAL SPACE.
THE DOMESTIC SPACE IS A
>> AND VERY OFTEN A VIOLENT
POLITICAL SPACE.
SPACE.
>> AND VERY OFTEN A VIOLENT
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE DOMESTIC
SPACE.
VIOLENCE TOWARDS WOMEN, IT TAKE
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE DOMESTIC
PLACE IN THE HOME.
VIOLENCE TOWARDS WOMEN, IT TAKE
IT'S NOT ONLY A PLACE OF
PLACE IN THE HOME.
TENDERNESS.
IT'S NOT ONLY A PLACE OF
IT'S ALSO A --
TENDERNESS.
[ NO AUDIO ]
VERY OFTEN A WOMAN WHO WANTS
MORE ARE PUNISHED FOR WANTING
MORE.
AND THIS WOMAN, SHE WANTS MORE,
SHE WANTS EXCITEMENT, SHE WANTS
DESIRE, SHE WANTS PASSION.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, SHE KNOWS
THAT SOCIETY HAS GIVEN HER VERY
MUCH BECAUSE SHE'S MARRIED TO A
DOCTOR OR SHE HAS A CHILD.
SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE SATISFIED,
SO SHE FEELS GUILTY FOR NOT
BEING SATISFIED AND SHE'S
LOOKING TO FILL THIS VOID WITH
SEX, BUT IT COULD BE WITH DRUGS
OR ALCOHOL OR GAMBLING
>> IT'S NOT JUST THAT SHE WANTS
MORE AND SHE WANTS PASSION AND
EXCITEMENT AND ALL THAT.
SHE GOES AND HAS SEX WITH
ANYBODY SHE SAYS.
PEOPLE SHE PICKS UP FROM THE
METRO IN THE SUBWAY, ANYONE.
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.
THAT'S WHY I WAS VERY INTERESTED
IN THE MECHANISM OF ADDICTION.
YOU WANT SOMETHING AND AT THE
SAME TIME YOU KNOW THIS THING IS
GOING TO DESTROY YOU AND YOU
CAN'T HELP IT, SO YOU TAKE THIS
THING AND THEN YOU HATE YOURSELF
FOR TAKING IT.
IT NEVER ENDS AND IT'S A LOT OF
SELF-HATRED AND I WANTED TO
DESCRIBE THAT.
>> AND YET YOU WOULD THINK IT
MIGHT DISRUPT HER MARRIAGE, HER
HUSBAND WOULD WALK OUT, BUT HE
DOESN'T.
HOW DOES HE REACT, THE HUSBAND.
>> THAT'S THE INTERESTING PART
FOR ME, THE LOVE STORY.
I WAS ASKING MYSELF THE
QUESTION, CAN YOU FORGIVE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
IS IT POSSIBLE TO FORGIVE
SOMEONE WHO LIED TO YOU FOR SO
MANY YEARS AND CHEATED ON YOU?
AND I THINK THAT THE HUSBAND IS
FASCINATED GOBY HIS WIFE.
HE KNOWS IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO
CONTROL HER THAT'S WHY HE WANTS
TO KEEP HER AND TELLS HER YOU
HAVE A DISEASE.
I'M A DOCTOR, I'M GOING TO CURE
THIS DISEASE AND I'M GOING TO
HELP YOU.
YOU'RE GOING TO HEAL.
BUT THE TRUTH IS, IT'S NOT THE
DISEASE.
IT'S SOMETHING ELSE
>> SPOILER ALERT, DO THEY STAY
TOGETHER?
>> YOU HAVE TO READ IT.
>> HOW MUCH OF IT IS
AUTOBIOGRAPHIC CAL?
YOU YOURSELF ARE FRENCH AND
MOROCCAN EXTRACTION.
LIKE MIRIAM IN LULLABY, YOU
YOURSELF ARE A JOURNALIST OR
WERE LIKE THE CHARACTER IN ADELE
>> IT'S VERY DIFFICULT FOR A
WRITER TO SAY WHAT WAS
AUTOBIOGRAPHIC OR NOT.
YOU SAY I AND YOU REALLY EXPRESS
THE TRUTH ABOUT YOURSELF.
IF YOU DECIDE TO WRITE FICTION,
EVERYTHING IS FICTION.
>> I WANT TO ASK YOU BECAUSE I'M
REALLY INTERESTED.
YOU WERE COVERING THE ARAB
SPRING IN TUNISIA, AND YOU GOT
ARRESTED THERE.
HOW DID THAT INFORM YOUR LIFE
EXPERIENCE, YOUR EXPERIENCE AS A
WRITER THEN?
>> I HAVE TO SAY I WAS A MOTHER
OF A YOUNG CHILD AT THAT TIME,
TRAVELING A LOT AND COMING HOME
AND LOOKING AT MY CHILD WHO I
WAS MISSING VERY VERY MUCH, AND
IT WAS HARD.
THAT'S A HARD JOB TO BE A
REPORTER AND TO TRAVEL A LOT.
SOMETIMES YOU FEEL VERY
FRUSTRATED BECAUSE YOU PUT SO
MUCH WORK AND SO MUCH ENERGY.
ONE WEEK AFTER, YOU HAVE TO
WRITE ANOTHER ARTICLE AND YOU
HAVE THE FEELING THAT EVERYBODY
FORGOT ABOUT THE PREVIOUS ONE.
SO I WAS MAYBE TOO FRUSTRATED
DISAPPOINTED WRITE BOOKS BECAUSE
BOOKS STAY.
>> WHY DID YOU GET ARRESTED?
>> YOU KNOW, IT WAS VERY COMMON
AT THAT TIME TO BE ARRESTED WHEN
YOU WERE A JOURNALIST A WOMAN,
AND A MUSLIM IN THE STREET,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU WERE TAKING
PHOTOGRAPHS.
>> SO WHEN YOU WERE COVERING THE
TO A KNEESIAN ARAB SPRING, WHICH
IS WHERE IT STARTED, WHAT DID
YOU FEEL?
YOU'RE A WOMAN FROM A MUSLIM
COUNTRY.
WHAT DID YOU FEEL ABOUT THE
CHANGING FACE OF WOMANHOOD,
PARTICULARLY IN THAT COUNTRY?
TUNISIA HAS TRIED TO REALLY
FULFILL THE PROMISES OF THE ARAB
SPRING
>> EVEN NOW I THINK IT'S A VERY,
VERY IMPORTANT COUNTRY FOR US
ARABS WHO ARE LIBERALS.
>> SECULAR, YOU MEAN.
>> EXACTLY.
IT'S AN EXTRAORDINARY COUNTRY
AND I FELT AT THAT TIME SO MUCH
JOY, AND I FELT PROUD FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE.
I FELT PROUD OF BEING A YOUNG
ARAB WOMAN BECAUSE THEY MAKE US
PROUD TO GO IN THE STREET.
I WAS SO BRAVE.
IT WAS A WONDERFUL MOMENT TO
LIVE.
>> I'M REALLY INTERESTED IN
HEARING YOU CALL YOURSELF A
YOUNG ARAB WOMAN.
YOU OBVIOUSLY REALLY EMBRACE AND
OWN ALL SIDES OF YOUR HERITAGE.
>> YEAH.
I'M ARAB, I'M FRENCH, I'M FROM
THE WEST, I'M FROM AFRICA.
>> WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF WHAT'S
GOING ON IN OUR SOCIETY STILL TO
THIS DAY WITH THE RACISM,
WHETHER IT'S BLACK AND WHITE IN
AMERICA, WHETHER IT'S ARAB AND
WHITE IN FRANCE, OR WHATEVER IT
MIGHT BE HERE.
YOU CAN SEE WHAT'S GOING ON ALL
OVER EUROPE.
DO YOU SEE A POSITIVE PART OR DO
YOU SEE THINGS AS TENSE WITHOUT
AS MUCH RESOLUTION AS MAYBE WE
WOULD HAVE HOPED IN 2019?
>> YEAH, I SEE THE TENSION, I
SEE THE VIOLENCE, BUT IF I'M
REALLY HONEST WITH YOU, I HAVE
TO SAY THAT I LIVE IN A GROOVE
WHERE THERE IS NO RACISM, WHERE
PEOPLE ARE VERY OPEN-MINDED.
I BELONG TO THE GROUP WHO TAKES
ADVANTAGE OF GLOBALIZATION.
I'M NOT A VICTIM OF
GLOBALIZATION.
I TRAVEL ALL THE TIME.
I SPEAK MANY LANGUAGES.
I GO TO NICE RESTAURANTS IN NICE
CITIES.
I READ BOOKS.
THE TRUTH IS I COULD TELL YOU
THAT I'M WORRIED THAT I SEE THIS
TENSION, THAT I'M A VICTIM OF
THIS OR THAT, BUT THAT'S NOT
TRUE.
THE TRUTH IS MY LIFE IS VERY
NICE BECAUSE I LIVE IN A BUBBLE.
THAT'S THE TRUTH.
>> BUT OTHERS IN FRANCE DON'T
LIVE IN A BUBBLE AND MANY PEOPLE
OF YOUR ORIGIN DON'T FEEL AS YOU
DO.
WHAT CAN THIS PRESIDENT MACRON
DO?
HE'S UNDER SO MUCH PRESSURE FROM
THE ZEAL ZAHN.
>> WELL, THE PROBLEM IS THIS GAP
I WAS TELLING YOU ABOUT, THIS
GAP BETWEEN A PART OF THE
COUNTRY WHO HAS THE FEELING THEY
ARE TAKING ADVANTAGE OF
GLOBALIZATION, WANT MORE EUROPE
AND OPEN BORDERS.
AND THE REST OF THE POPULATION
WHO ARE A VICTIM OF THIS
GLOBALIZATION AND FINDS THEIR
LIFE IS GETTING WORSE AND WORSE.
IS PROBLEM IS THIS GAP.
HOW DO WE LIVE SNOGT HOW IS IT
POSSIBLE TO REBUILD OUR SOCIETY
AND TO FIND GOALS THAT ARE THE
GOALS OF EVERYONE, AND NOT ONLY
OF A FEW.
>> ON THE ME TOO ISSUE, YOU
REMEMBER WHEN IT ALL STARTED.
AND THEN THERE WAS A LETTER, AN
OPEN LETTER BY, AMONG OTHER
PEOPLE, THE FAMOUS ACTRESS
CATHERINE DID HE NERVE AND
OTHERS.
WE SHOULD HAVE THE RIGHT TO BE
LOOKED AT, STARED AT, TO BE
WANTED, DESIRED, ALL OF THIS ME
TOO IS GOING TOO FAR.
AND YOU WROTE A REBUTTAL, AN
OPEN-LETTER REBUTTAL WHERE YOU
SAID --
>> WE SHOULD HAVE THE RIGHT NOT
TO BE BULLIED, HARASSED, ET
CETERA.
I SAID YOU SHOULD LOOK A LITTLE
BIT OUT OF FRANCE AND LOOK AT
THE SITUATION OF WOMEN IN EGYPT,
IN PERU, KONG GO, PAKISTAN.
THE LIFE OF WOMEN THERE IS NOT
LIKE THE LIFE IN PARIS WHERE YOU
WANT KNOWN LOOK AT YOU AND TO
TELL YOU YOU'RE PRETTY.
THAT'S A PROBLEM THERE.
>> DO YOU THINK THEY GET IT NOW,
THIS OLDER GENERATION OF WOMEN?
>> YES, I THINK, I THINK, I
THINK AT THE BEGINNING IT WAS
DIFFICULT BECAUSE THEY WERE
AFRAID THAT FRANCE WAS GOING TO
LOSE SOMETHING IN TERMS OF
LIBERTY AND PHILOSOPHY OF
GALLANTRY.
NOW THEY UNDERSTAND THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN DEFENDING
THIS CULTURE AND DEFENDING WOMEN
AND THE RIGHT OF WOMEN TO BE
SAFE.
>> I WANT TO ASK YOU ALSO ABOUT
RACE.
YOU DON'T OVERTLY DISCUSS RACE
OR WRITE ABOUT IT, BUT IT'S
STILL A SUBTEXT IN A LOT OF WHAT
YOU WRITE.
JAMES BALDWIN, THE GREAT
AMERICAN WRITER, BLACK, CAME TO
PARIS BECAUSE HE COULDN'T GET
THE SPACE THAT HE NEEDED IN THE
UNITED STATES.
AND HE IS STILL SO RELEVANT
TODAY.
ONE OF THE LAST BOOKS HE WROTE,
IF BEAL STREET COULD TALK, A
MAJOR MOVIE, OSCAR NOMINATED,
ALL SORTS OF AWARDS.
ARE YOU SURPRISED THAT HE AND
THAT KIND OF WRITING REMAINS SO
RELEVANT TODAY STILL?
SO RAW?
>> NO.
I'M NOT SURPRISED.
UNFORTUNATELY I'M NOT SURPRISED.
ESPECIALLY IN THE U.S.
I'M VERY INTERESTED IN THE
QUESTIONS OF RACE ISSUE IN THE
U.S.
FOR FRENCH-MOROCCAN AM WWOMAN,
SURPRISED.
A FEW DAYS AGO I WAS WATCHING A
DOCUMENTARY WITH MY SON ABOUT
THE SITUATION OF BLACK PEOPLE IN
THE '60s AND SEGREGATION.
IT'S HARD TO EXPLAIN THAT BLACK
PEOPLE COULDN'T SIT IN THE BUS.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY, CAN YOU
TELL ME WHY?
NO, I CAN'T.
I CAN'T TELL YOU WHY.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO EXPLAIN TO A
CHILD.
THIS VIOLENCE REMAINS NOT ONLY
THERE BUT REMAINS ALSO IN
EUROPE.
IF YOU SEE THE SITUATION IN
HUNKER AND ITALY, THE RACISM
NOW.
AND IN THE SOUTH OF SPAIN NOW,
THE EXTREME RIGHT.
THAT'S VERY, VERY -- I'M VERY
PESSIMISTIC, ACTUALLY
>> YOU ARE VERY PESSIMISTIC?
>> YEAH, BECAUSE ALL THE WORST
THINGS HAPPENED.
>> KEEP HAPPENING.
>> EXACTLY.
>> TALKING ABOUT BALDWIN, A
RECENT ARTICLE IN THE "FINANCIAL
TIMES" CALLED HIM, QUOTE, A
SOLDIER, A COMRADE.
HE'S A BROTHER IN ARMS IN A WAR
THAT DOESN'T END.
DO YOU FEEL THIS IS A WAR THAT
DOESN'T END?
>> YES, IT'S A WAR THAT DOESN'T
END, BUT AT THE SAME TIME, WHAT
MAKES ME OPTIMISTIC IS THAT
TODAY WE TALK OF JAMES BALDWIN
AND TODAY THIS KIND OF
INTELLECTUAL MATTERS ARE
IMPORTANT IN THE DEBATE.
I WAS WORKING A FEW MONTHS AGO
WITH A GROUP OF PEOPLE FROM
DIFFERENT UNIVERSITIES IN EUROPE
ABOUT COLONIALISM, ABOUT RACE,
AND ABOUT FEMINISM.
IT'S VERY INTERESTING BECAUSE
NOW WE ARE TALKING ABOUT TOPICS
THAT WERE NOT RELEVANT 50 YEARS
AGO, SO IT'S GOING TO CHANGE.
WHAT MAKES ME OPTIMISTIC ABOUT
THAT NOW, PEOPLE FROM THE SOUTH
LIKE ME, BUT PEOPLE COMING FROM
AFRICA ARE VERY IMPORTANT IN THE
DEBATE AND WE CAN SPEAK OF OTHER
TOPICS SAND GIVE OTHER POINTS O
VIEW AND I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT.
>> AMAZING TIME.
LEILA SLIMANI, THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> WE HOPE YOU ENJOYED THOSE
CONVERSATIONS TO END THIS WEEK.
THAT'S IT FOR OUR PROGRAM
TONIGHT.
THANKS FOR WATCHING "AMANPOUR &
CO." ON PBS AND JOIN US AGAIN
NEXT TIME.
>>> UNIWORLD IS A PROUD SPONSOR
OF "AMANPOUR & CO."
WHEN BEA TOLLMAN'S 60-YEAR
CULINARY CAREER BEGAN, SHE
DIDN'T KNOW THE RECIPES FROM HER
COOK BOOK WOULD MAKE THEIR WAY
TO HER RIVER CRUISE LINE,
UNIWORLD.
BEA'S LOCALLY INSPIRED CUISINE
IS SERVED WHILE CRUISING THROUGH
EUROPE, ASIA, INDIA, AND EGYPT
BECAUSE, ACCORDING TO BEA, TO
TRAVEL IS TO EAT.
BOOKINGS AVAILABLE THROUGH YOUR
TRAVEL ADVISER.
FOR MORE INFORMATION, VISIT
UNIWORLD.COM.
>> ADDITIONAL SUPPORT HAS BEEN
PROVIDED BY ROSALIND P. WALTER,
BERNARD AND IRENE SCHWARTZ, SUE
AND EDGAR WACHENHEIM III, THE
CHERYL AND PHILIP MILSTEIN
FAMILY, SETON MELVIN, JUDY AND
JOSH WESTON, THE JPB FOUNDATION,
AND BY CONTRIBUTIONS TO YOUR PBS
STATION FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.
THANK YOU.
>>> YOU ARE WATCHING PBS.
(piano music)
♪
(theme music)
(growls)
(whimpers)
♪
(Martin)
How long have you been up for?
(Louisa)
Oh, an hour or so,
I couldn't sleep.
-Did James wake you?
-No, I've just been trying
to write my resignation letter.
-I'm just struggling with it.
-Why?
(Louisa)
Because I've been at the school
since I was five, Martin.
(Martin)
I thought you'd made
your mind up.
(Louisa)
Well, yes, I have.
-You're overstretched.
-I know.
(Martin)
Do you want me
to write it for you?
(Louisa)
No, it's--
it's just difficult.
(Martin)
It shouldn't be.
"Dear so-and-so,
I am writing to inform you
that I would like
to hand in my resignation
from the position
of headmistress."
(Louisa)
Martin, really,
it's not helping.
(soft music)
(whimpers)
♪
(music brightens)
(Buffy)
Three.
Four.
Five.
-Six.
-Come on!
(Buffy)
Seven.
-Eight.
-This is great!
(Buffy)
Nine!
Ten!
-Everybody all right?
-Yeah.
(chattering)
♪
-There we go.
-All right, ship oars!
♪
(Alice)
All right.
Okay, get yourselves ready.
Training starts
in ten minutes sharp.
(Joe)
Ms. Taylor.
Welcome back to Portwenn.
(Alice)
PC Penhale.
You're looking good.
Have you been working out?
(Joe)
As umpire this year,
I'd like a nice clean race.
-Unlike last year.
-I think you'll find
that we beat you
fair and square last year.
(Joe)
Only on a technicality,
after a rather
protracted appeal.
Not so square and fair.
(Alice)
Well, I don't make the rules.
I just know them better
than anyone else,
apparently.
(Joe)
Really?
What's rule 20, then?
(Alice)
All gigs must complete races
by following the course
as instructed.
(Joe)
Actually, you're wrong.
Nope, you're right.
(Samantha)
Hold up!
(Morwenna)
I think we're definitely
getting better.
(Samantha)
Huh! That's debatable.
(Alice)
Good morning.
(Morwenna)
(Alice)
Looking good.
(Morwenna)
Thank you.
(Alice)
Hm.
(tittering)
Come on then.
Let's go.
-They look properly confident.
-'Course they're confident.
They've won four in a row.
(Eric)
Well, Ellie,
like I always say,
it's what you do today
that counts, not yesterday.
All we need to do
is follow Eric's lead.
He's in the stroke position,
he's setting the rhythm.
I think we've got
a real chance.
-Argh!
-Ooh!
-Dad?
-I'm okay, I'm okay.
-Move the boat!
-All right. Move the boat.
Keep moving her forwards.
(Samantha)
Good one, Pippa.
You just crocked
our best rower.
(Pippa)
It weren't my fault.
(Ellie)
What's happened?
Is it your hand?
-My finger.
-Oh, man up!
I'm sure its not as bad
as you think.
(Eric)
I'll head up to the doc's,
see if he can fix it.
Ellie, you'll need to cover
for me at the fish stall.
(Ellie)
What? I didn't even wanna
do this in the first place.
-All your idea.
-Ellie!
(Ellie)
And now I've got
to work at the stall
and wear that stupid hat
and stink of fish?
(Eric)
I'm in a lot of pain right now.
So, please,
open up the fish stall.
(groans)
(Joe)
What's wrong with your leg?
Not that there's anything wrong
with your legs.
(Alice)
It's an old training injury.
It's what they call dedication.
(Joe)
Dedication looks pretty painful.
(Louisa)
So I'll see you
at the garage at five.
I'm so sorry
I can't meet for lunch.
Bye, sweetie.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
-Bye.
-Morwenna,
stop messing around
with boats
and go and open the surgery.
(Morwenna)
Well, I need to go
get changed.
(Joe)
Doc, a minute of your time.
This is Dr. Ellingham.
He'll have a look
at your legs--leg.
(Alice)
Yes, it's actually--
it's quite painful now, so--
(Martin)
If you want a consultation,
make an appointment.
Well, you could just
tell me what it is.
It's a leg, if you want me
to diagnose your condition,
make an appointment
and come to the surgery.
"It's a leg"!
(Bert)
Al! Al!
A little bit of help.
I'm very busy, Dad.
Al! Al...
-What is it?
-I'm in agony up here.
(sighs)
Right.
Okay!
(Bert)
Oi.
You took your time.
(Al)
I'm packing cases.
-What's happened?
-It's my foot.
(sighs)
You've got to get me
up the hill
to see the doctor.
(Al)
What, now?
No, no,
not if it's inconvenient.
I'm about to pass out
'cause of the excruciating pain
that is throbbing
through my toe.
But if you'd rather wait,
you know,
have a bit of breakfast,
read the paper.
(soft music)
♪
(chattering)
(Martin)
Would you take James, please?
What's wrong with your arm?
Nothing, it's just a rash.
-Let me see.
-It came up overnight.
-Looks like lichen planus.
-What's that, then?
-Is it contagious?
-No, come to the surgery.
I'll prescribe you
something for it,
but don't scratch it!
You'll make it worse.
Goodbye, James.
Have a good day.
(thudding and clattering)
(Graham)
Ohh!
Ooh!
(Martin)
You all right?
(grunts)
Don't make a fuss, Doc.
I've got to get to work.
Just tripped on the last step.
(Mel)
Ignore him, Doc.
He's got two left feet.
It's all right,
Doc says it's not contagious.
(Joe)
How's the leg?
(sighs)
(Alice)
I thought
it'd be better by now.
(Joe)
Ooh!
-The size of that lump!
-Oh.
It wasn't as big as that
this morning.
Maybe I should go and see
that doctor of yours.
(Joe)
I strongly advise you do.
As umpire,
I have discretion to decide
if people are physically fit
for the competition or not.
-Also, that looks terrifying.
-Yes, fine,
I'll go see that
Dr. Ellington after practice.
-Ellingham.
-What?
It's Dr. Ellingham.
-"Gham."
-Right.
(Joe)
It's up there.
Just tell him
Joe Penhale sent you.
-He'll know what you mean.
-Oh, right.
So he'll see me quicker
if I mention your name?
(Joe)
Probably not, no.
(Alice)
So why did you bring this up?
You were trying
to impress me.
-Did it impress you?
-No.
-Think you can fix it?
-It's not broken.
It's dislocated.
Look that way.
(Eric)
Argh!
Bit of warning next time, Doc.
-You feel that?
-Yeah.
Good, I'll need to splint that
and bandage it.
(Eric)
How long will that be for?
(Martin)
Come back and see me
in three days,
but it will need to stay bound
for at least two weeks.
(Eric)
No, no, no, Doc,
we've got the race.
(Martin)
No, you're not racing.
(Eric)
There's got to be a way.
I've convinced my Ellie
to get involved.
Spends most of her time
on her bloody phone.
She's gonna be pretty annoyed
if she has to row without me.
Can't you just give it
an injection or something?
(Martin)
You need to rest your hand
to avoid doing further
and more serious damage
to yourself.
-This is important.
-No, it's not.
It's a boat race.
-So?
-Sorry, Morwenna.
Oh, Doc, wasn't there
anything else you could do?
(Martin)
No, there wasn't.
(Bert)
Doc, can you help me here?
-Yes, go through.
-Oh, thanks.
(Eric)
You know if I could race,
I would.
(Morwenna)
Where am I gonna find somebody
last minute to take your place?
(Al)
Oh, no, no,
I mean, I wish I could,
I really do but I need
to look after the pub tomorrow,
especially
as Dad's not so well.
Oh, cheers.
-It's gout.
-Gout?
But I don't drink port, Doc.
(Martin)
Gout's got nothing to do
with port.
Babies get gout.
There's often
a genetic predisposition
towards a high level
of uric acid in the blood.
(Bert)
Well, that's very interesting,
Doc, but I'm in agony here.
(Martin)
Yes, I'll prescribe you
naproxen to dull the pain
and also test your blood
to see if you'd benefit
from allopurinol, but that's
a long-term solution.
(Bert)
I just need to get back
on my feet so I can help Al.
Isn't there some quick fix
you can give me?
(Martin)
No, it doesn't work like that.
Keep your foot
raised for a week,
put an ice-pack on your toe,
and drink plenty of water.
(Morwenna)
Well, if you can't help me,
can you think
of anyone else who can?
(Al)
Well, you used to row,
didn't you, Mr. Cleveland?
(Mr. Cleveland)
I did, yes.
In fact, I rowed alongside
your grandfather, Morwenna.
(Morwenna)
Really? I didn't know that.
(Mr. Cleveland)
Before your time, of course.
If you're in a real bind
I suppose I could get
into the boat again and--
(coughs)
(Morwenna)
You're all right, Mr. C.
I'm sure we'll find someone.
Thanks though.
Oh. All right, Alice?
(Alice)
I'd like to make an appointment
with Dr. Ellington.
(Al)
Oh, it's Ellingham, Ellingham.
(Morwenna)
Yeah, Ellingham.
I should be able to squeeze you
in in about an hour.
-Is there nothing earlier?
-I'm in no rush.
(coughs)
She can--she can go before me.
(Morwenna)
Oh.
(Alice)
I hear you're a man down.
I do hope you find someone.
Won't be much of a contest
otherwise.
-Mind you.
-Yeah,
maybe this year
will be different, eh?
Take a seat.
(Alice)
Maybe.
-Everything okay, Dad?
-I've got gout, boy.
I've got to put my leg up
for a week.
-What about the pub?
-I'm the invalid here.
-Next patient?
-Alice Taylor.
She's from Port Carran,
but I'll register her
as a temporary patient.
-Yes. Come through.
-Thanks.
-Morning, Bert.
-Hello, Janet.
-What, a whole week?
-Well, I could try
and get up for lunch
and dinner,
but how about
breakfast in bed, eh?
(student)
♪ We'll man all the boats
and we'll head out to sea ♪
(group)
♪ Wey, hey, blow the man down ♪
(student)
Um...
♪ Out on the waves now,
so wild and so free ♪
(group)
♪ Whoa, give me some time
to blow the man down ♪
(Louisa)
I've got something to tell you.
I've made a big decision.
(Pippa)
You're leaving Martin?
(Louisa)
No!
I've decided
to give in my notice.
-I think.
-You think?
(Louisa)
Well, I was sure,
but it's easy to say it,
and it's harder
to actually do it.
And I'll miss the kids
and the school and -
-That must be so tough.
-Mm.
If you did leave,
do you think
I'd get your job?
(Louisa)
I've no idea.
(Pippa)
No, of course.
You could write me a reference
though, if you wanted.
-No pressure.
-Pippa.
(group)
♪ Whoa, give me some time
to blow the man down ♪♪
(Louisa)
It's fine. I think it'll
be good on the actual day.
They just need
to learn their lines.
(Alice)
It's been hurting for a while.
My GP had a look,
but it's just blown up.
(Martin)
Mm, it's a Baker's cyst.
They can come up very quickly.
-Well, it sounds manageable.
-No.
It needs to be dealt with.
If it bursts, which it looks
like it could at any moment,
and the fluid leaks
into your calf,
then the pain
will be excruciating.
(Alice)
Well, if you deal with it, I'll
be able to row tomorrow, yes?
(Martin)
Yes, I'll draw out the fluid
and put a dressing
on it for you.
(Alice)
So will you cut it open?
(Martin)
No, I'll insert a needle
and draw it out with a syringe.
(Alice)
No, I have this--I have
this thing with needles.
(Martin)
It's the only way,
you won't feel anything.
(Alice)
No, I had a terrible experience
with needles as a child.
I had jaundice.
A lot of blood was taken.
It was very painful.
(Martin)
Right, well,
that's understandable.
(Alice)
No, if you stick a needle in me,
I might throw up.
My GP normally gives me
lorazepam, a sedative.
(Martin)
I don't prescribe
unnecessary medicines.
Does your watch
have a second hand?
-Yes.
-Good.
Lie down and look
at your watch
and count the seconds
out loud.
Come on.
♪
(Alice)
20, 21.
Right, this is just
a local anesthetic.
♪
25, 26, 27,
28, 29, 30, 31...
-What's that for?
-In case you vomit.
♪
41, 42, 43,
44, 45, 46,
47, 48, 49,
50, 51, 52,
53, 54...
♪
-Oh, no, no, no, no.
-What are you doing?
-Get that thing away from me!
-Come on, don't be silly.
-Come on.
-Oh, God!
Oh.
(tense music)
♪
(clears throat)
(Morwenna)
Wake up!
(slap)
Doc!
You okay?
(slap)
Stop hitting me.
Oh, God,
is she still bleeding?
-Everything okay?
-What? Get out!
(Morwenna)
Go on.
(Martin)
Morwenna, I need plasters
and butterfly stitches.
(Morwenna)
All right.
You know you were both
unconscious?
On the floor?
What, he passed out too?
Why did you pass out?
(Alice)
I hate needles.
What have I done to my head?
(Morwenna)
You must have hit it
when you fell.
(Alice)
Oh! I told you.
You didn't listen.
Now look at me.
I have a cup to win tomorrow.
(Martin)
No.
You should stay at home.
(Alice)
You're not fit to practice.
You are a liability.
(Martin)
Just go home
and get some rest.
(Alice)
No. The way you've treated me
is disgraceful.
(Martin)
What do you mean,
I've drained your cyst
and I've dressed
your head wound.
(Alice)
What, the head wound
inflicted by you.
-Don't be absurd.
-Okay.
(Morwenna)
Do you want me
to call you a taxi?
No, I can--
I can walk.
(Janet)
Lying on the floor,
both of them.
-What, seriously?
-Yeah.
(soft music)
♪
(knocking)
Yes?
♪
(Morwenna)
Do you want me
to cancel your patients?
(Martin)
Why would I do that?
(Morwenna)
Well, in case you're,
you know, not feeling well.
(Martin)
No, I'm fine.
Thank you.
Show them in.
(Morwenna)
All right, um--oh.
Mel's here.
She's a bit early
but she's got to go.
Yes, come through.
Take a seat.
Thank you.
Show me your wrist.
(Mel)
Are you all right?
I heard you fainted.
(Martin)
It's lichen planus.
Nobody knows
where it comes from,
and there's nothing you could
have done to prevent it.
I'll prescribe you
a corticosteroid cream
to soothe
the irritation.
Do you wash yourself with soap?
(Mel)
Of course, there's nothing
wrong with my hygiene.
The soap will be
drying your skin out,
increasing the itching.
From now on, just wash with
water but do keep washing.
(Mel)
Will it go away?
(Martin)
It should do.
Between six and nine months.
What's wrong with your arm?
(Mel)
Oh, Graham fell over
and knocked into it.
-Who's Graham?
-Graham.
My husband Graham.
You met him this morning.
(Martin)
Oh. Does he fall over a lot?
(Mel)
Sometimes.
(Martin)
Do you think he has
a problem with alcohol?
(Mel)
No!
He has the occasional beer,
very occasional,
but I'd know
if there was a problem.
-Well, you might not.
-Are you saying
-he's lying to me?
-I'm not saying anything.
Just get him
to come and see me.
-He wouldn't come here.
-Why not? Just ask him.
You're very abrasive.
I'm sure he'd do what you said.
(Mel)
Yes. Right.
Thanks.
(Al)
Any luck?
No.
Half the village
don't want to row
'cause they think
we're gonna lose,
and the other half are
physically incapable.
(Bert)
Put me in the second camp.
I have every faith
in your ability.
Chippy said you'd put
Port Carran down
as odds-on favorites to win.
(Bert)
I'm in a lot of pain
and wish to be left alone.
Now.
(Morwenna)
Come on, Al. Please.
(Al)
Oh, last time I got in a boat,
I smashed a woman
in the face with the oar
and burst her nose open.
-I remember that.
-It was an accident.
Morwenna,
I'd love to help
but I've got this place, so...
(Bert)
The pub
is gonna open later now.
I promised Louisa
I'd go up to the school
and help sell tickets
and programs.
(Morwenna)
That is very kind of you, Bert.
Doing something for the good
of the village.
If only there were more people
like you about.
(tuts)
(Al)
If I don't say yes,
you're gonna keep asking me
-and asking me, aren't you?
-No, no, no.
If you're too scared
to get in a boat,
that's no problem at all.
(Al)
I'm not scared.
I'm not.
Okay.
I'll row.
Yeah.
Hm.
Yes?
(Alice)
Hello, uh,
I'd like some paracetamol,
please.
(Sally)
Oh, dear.
What's happened to you?
(Alice)
I passed out
in the doctor's surgery.
(Sally)
Oh.
(Alice)
That doctor passed out too.
It was quite the scene.
(Sally)
What?
Is he all right?
He's fine.
Something to do with seeing
my blood all over the floor.
(Sally)
Oh, yes,
he's a martyr.
(Alice)
Oh, really?
In what way?
(Sally)
Oh, it's an affliction,
a phobia.
He's had it
ever since he came here.
Before he came here.
Actually why
he had to leave London.
And he fights through it,
each and every day.
(Alice)
Thank you.
(sinister music)
You've been very helpful.
(Sally)
45p, please.
Thank you.
♪
(Louisa)
But why do you think
you fainted?
(Martin)
I don't know.
(Louisa)
Has your blood phobia got worse?
(Martin)
No, I don't think so.
I thought you had it
under control.
(Martin)
Yes, I do have it under control.
Look, I thought
we were looking for a car.
What about this one?
This one's practical.
No.
(Graham)
Louisa, Doc.
-Hello, there.
-I like this one.
(Graham)
Oh, it's cheap to run.
You can park it anywhere.
You can take it for
a test drive, if you like.
(Martin)
You're slurring your words.
-Have you been drinking?
-Absolutely not.
Have you been talking
to my wife?
(Louisa)
Martin. Yes, I'd love to take it
for a test drive.
-That would be great.
-I shall get the keys.
-This one?
-Mm.
I think it's fun.
(Martin)
Fun?
(wiper blades squeak)
-It's very small, isn't it?
-Mm.
(Martin)
Where would you put
the child seat?
(Louisa)
It's fine.
I can put it in the front.
-Where would I sit?
-Well, it's not really meant
for family outings.
It's just to help me get
to and from college.
(Martin)
Yes, change out of third now.
(Louisa)
Yeah, I know what I'm doing.
(Martin)
It's been a long time
since you drove.
(Louisa)
Martin, shush.
Oh, by the way, are you
coming up to the school
-to watch the race tomorrow?
-I hadn't planned to.
(Louisa)
You know it'll be my last time
doing the performance.
It would mean a lot
if you were there.
(Martin)
Mirror.
Have you handed in
your letter of resignation?
-Mm. Mostly.
-What do you mean?
(Louisa)
I mean I've written the letter.
I just haven't officially
passed it over yet, as it were.
-I don't know what that means.
-It means I haven't
-handed it in yet.
-Why not?
(Louisa)
Because, Martin, I haven't.
Can you just let me concentrate
on the road, please?
-Very close on this side.
-Yes.
-And slowly round the corners.
I have actually driven a car
before.
(Martin)
Not this one.
(soft music)
(Graham)
What were you thinking,
running your mouth off
in front of the doc
and everyone?
(Mel)
Because I'm worried about you.
A couple of times a week,
you're completely sozzled.
(Graham)
I am not.
Why can't you trust me?
(Mel)
I'm not stupid, you know.
You should go and see him.
-Right, so how did we find it?
-Yeah, I like it.
(Martin)
Well, obviously we're going
to look at other cars.
(Louisa)
No, no, I'm going to buy it.
(Graham)
Well, I'll get
the paperwork organized,
give the car a once-over,
and we can drop it off
tomorrow, then.
(Louisa)
Thank you.
What?
It's my money, Martin.
Yes, I understand that, but...
(Louisa)
But what?
-But nothing.
-It's a nice car.
It's a good decision.
♪
(banging on door)
(Mel)
Doc, sorry it's late,
but you did say if Graham
wanted to talk.
(Martin)
Yes, come in.
(Mel)
So, we had a talk,
and he still says
he's not drinking.
-I'm not!
-Well, something's going on,
isn't it?
(Graham)
Well, that's why
I've come here, Doc.
You see, some nights
I'm swaying all over the place
and the next day
I feel awful.
I'm--I'm worried
that it might be...
might be Parkinson's.
(Martin)
What makes you think that?
(Graham)
Well, I was looking it up
and I've got
the same symptoms.
(Martin)
Really?
Do you have any
of the following:
tremors or stiffness,
sight problems, cramps,
difficulty swallowing,
dribbling?
(Graham)
Sometimes I have stomach cramps.
-Not the others?
-No.
(Martin)
It's not Parkinson's.
-Diet?
-Uh, no, not me.
-What is your diet?
-Oh, um,
a bit of cheese,
bit of bread, chicken.
Mel here cooks up
a lot of pies,
like shepherd's,
cottage, fish.
(Martin)
Stop talking.
I need you to blow into this.
This will indicate
any alcohol on your breath.
(Graham)
Well, you're wasting
your time there, Doc,
'cause I know for sure
that I don't.
(Martin)
Let me see.
Well, this says that you do.
The equivalent of two
or three glasses of wine.
-Or cider.
-Something you want
to tell me, Graham?
-It can't be right.
-It's a medical fact.
Or are you gonna argue
with facts now?
(Martin)
I'll take a blood sample.
Measure the alcohol in that.
(Mel)
Don't pass out, Doc.
(Graham)
I just--I just don't
understand it, Doc.
I mean, I don't even remember
the last time I had a drink,
it were that long ago.
(Mel)
Well, you have been
stressed at work.
If you tell me the truth,
Graham, right now,
I promise I won't be mad.
-I am telling the truth.
-Oh, for goodness sake.
(Martin)
Until I get your blood sample
results back, you can't drive.
(Graham)
I've got to deliver
Louisa's car.
(Mel)
I can do that.
You wait for me outside.
I just need a minute
to talk to the doc
about that rash of mine.
So?
(Martin)
I told you before,
it's lichen planus.
(Mel)
No, not about me!
Graham!
He's got a lot
of faults, Doc,
but being a liar's
not one of 'em.
-At least, I didn't think so.
-Well, if he is an alcoholic,
they can often be very secretive
about their drinking.
See if you can find
some evidence.
(Mel)
I'll watch him
like a hawk, Doc.
(Martin)
Yes.
♪
-Good morning, Constable.
-Oh!
(Alice)
Oh, sorry, did I scare you?
(Joe)
No, not at all.
It's just
I'm trained to react
so it could
have been dangerous.
-Right.
-Shouldn't really creep up
-on me like that.
-Well, I hope you're not
-sabotaging our gig.
-Just measuring the boat.
As umpire, I take
my impartiality very seriously.
Ms. Taylor,
are you sure
you're feeling well enough
to compete?
-What?
-Did the doc say
-you're okay to race?
-Yes, fine.
It was just a cyst.
He jabbed it
with a needle,
drained it,
then collapsed.
Any other questions?
I was meant to get
married this year,
but my wife more or less
left me at the altar.
What was meant to be
the greatest day of my life
turned out
to be the worst.
(Alice)
And?
(Joe)
Sometimes we think
we're doing well
when actually we're not,
but we're so determined
to make things right,
we don't notice.
(Alice)
Yeah, well, thank you
for being so considerate.
-Sorry you got jilted.
-It's okay.
But the only thing
that matters
is that we won last year.
And the year before.
And we will win
this year again.
Have you never heard
of the expression,
"It's not the winning that
counts, it's the taking part?"
(Alice)
Yes, but only by the people
who don't win.
Excuse me.
(Mel)
You can take them
down to the fundraiser
at the end of the day,
but don't forget to put
their reins on,
-all right?
-Okay.
-Really?
-Just checking.
(Graham)
You've been checking on me
all night and all morning.
Even got up in
the middle of the night
when I went
to the bloody bathroom.
(grunts)
That was an accident.
-Don't leave stuff in the boat.
-I didn't mean to.
(Alice)
Hold it!
Okay, keep it level while
we just do final checks.
(Ellie)
They look so much better
than us.
(Morwenna)
It's not about how they look.
It's about what they do.
(Pippa)
You mean like winning
four years in a row?
(Morwenna)
All right! But we've got
something they haven't.
-Oh, please don't say heart.
-No, I wasn't gonna say that.
It's been ages since
Portwenn tasted victory.
And last year
we came so close
only for Port Carran
to rob us of that trophy.
But this year,
we're taking it back.
Because today,
today is our day for glory!
That's when
you're meant to start
clapping and cheering, guys.
(siren blaring)
(Caitlin)
Oh, God.
Who gave him that?
(Eric)
Oh, here we go.
(Joe)
Right, listen up, everyone.
Gather 'round.
Come on, yep.
I want you
to get into your gigs
and go to the starting line.
The bull horn will signal
the start of the race.
I want you to row out, around
the buoy and then back again.
The first team
to cross the finishing line
will be the winner.
May the best team win.
(Alice)
Good luck, Portwenn.
♪
(Caitlin)
I hope they drown.
♪
(Eric)
Let's get this over with.
♪
(Bert)
Oi, oi, oi!
Here's your program
and ticket.
Would you like to place a bet
on the winner of the race?
(attendee)
Is that for charity as well?
(Bert)
Only if you bet on Portwenn.
(attendee)
No, thank you.
(Joe)
So, here we are,
ladies and gentlemen.
Make sure you stop by a stall.
Don't want
any stingy people here.
There's the raffle,
if you fancy your chances.
I've bought 20 tickets,
so better win
something this year.
♪
(Ruth)
Louisa?
Oh, very nautical.
(Louisa)
I just thought
I'd make an effort.
(Ruth)
Here.
Let me.
-Thank you.
-Is Martin here?
I wanted to have a word
with him.
(Louisa)
He's most likely holed up
in the surgery avoiding people.
I had asked him
to come down
as it's probably
gonna be my last fundraiser,
but you know Martin.
Sorry, excuse me, Ruth.
David, you're late,
where's your costume?
-Yes, well, go on.
-There's Mrs. Thompson's
famous sponge cake.
Probably the only thing around
here that doesn't float.
Right?
No.
To be fair,
Mrs. Thompson,
with all you've gone through,
I'm amazed you even get up
in the morning,
let alone bake a cake.
So, Morwenna used
to have a fear of rowing,
but fortunately
that ship has sailed.
♪
Martin,
are you here?
♪
Ruth.
(Ruth)
I heard about your fainting.
Why didn't you come
and see me about it?
-It was a one-off.
-Well, everything is a one-off
until it happens again.
And what does Louisa mean
when she says
this is her last fundraiser?
(Martin)
She's stopping teaching.
She's going to concentrate
on her course
-full-time now.
-Oh, good.
-And that's fine with you?
-Yes.
Yes, we've discussed it.
It's a good decision.
(Ruth)
But why are you
hiding here, then,
when she wants you to join her
up at the fundraiser?
-I'm not hiding.
-Oh, good.
Then you can walk me
back up there.
-Come on.
-Yes.
You do realize
there'll be children singing
and the whole thing
will be ghastly, don't you?
Well, don't say
I didn't warn you.
(Graham)
Um, a slice of the sponge,
please, a large one.
(seller)
Okay, that's £2.50.
-Mel.
-Ooh,
I didn't realize
it was fancy dress.
(Louisa)
Well, it's not really, you know.
How's James?
When are they coming down?
(Mel)
The little 'uns
are all up at the nursery.
They're bringing them down
at the end of the day.
(Louisa)
Yes, it's best when
it's a bit quieter, I think.
(Graham)
And one of these
for my little friend here.
(Joe)
Right, everyone
pay attention to me!
Everyone looking at me!
Everyone!
Right, the race
is about to start.
(cheering, applause)
(tense music)
♪
(heavy breathing)
Rowers, are you ready?
Three, two, one...
(klaxon)
(lively music)
And they're off!
(rowers communicating)
♪
And we're off to a good start.
The boats will head out
around the buoy
and then they'll disappear
for a while, which,
to be honest,
is pretty boring.
So, in the meantime,
the children are
gonna perform for us.
Let's hope
it's not quite so boring.
I'm sure it won't,
fingers crossed.
(student)
A long time ago, the Cornish gig
was a work boat,
taking pilots out to ships
in the stormy Atlantic.
(student)
They would race to get jobs
and argued about which village
had the fastest boats.
(student)
Which is why,
for years and years,
Portwenn and Port Carran
have battled it out
for the annual Gig Cup.
(student)
♪ We'll man all our boats
and we'll head out to sea ♪
♪ Wey, hey, blow the man down ♪
(sings drunkenly)
(students)
♪ Whoa! Give me some time
to blow the man down ♪
-Blow the man down!
-Be quiet!
(attendee)
Oi, keep it down, eh?
Might want to go easy
on the beer as well.
-I'm not drinking!
-Sound like you have to me.
(Mel)
He hasn't. I've been
watching him all day.
(Louisa)
Mel, he does seem
a little worse for wear.
(Mel)
Louisa, I swear, if he'd been
drinking, I'd know about it.
(Louisa)
Why don't you
just take him home?
Really.
(Mel)
Graham.
Graham?
(students)
♪ Whoa! ♪
♪ Give me some time
to blow the man down ♪♪
(cheering, applause)
(Joe)
Thank you very much
to the children
of Portwenn School there.
Not that boring after all.
♪
(rowers communicating)
(Morwenna)
Five, six.
(rower)
Seven, eight!
Come on,
put your backs into it!
-Oh!
-Oh, Al!
We're losing ground!
Come on!
-Sorry, it was an accident.
-Absolutely useless!
(Al)
I told you
I was rubbish at rowing.
(Caitlin)
No domestics!
Get back to work!
One, two, three.
Come on!
Four, five, six.
-Round the mark!
-Come on.
-Here they come,
around the buoy!
Portwenn have
got it all to do
as Port Carran
open up a lead!
The race is definitely
in Port Carran's favor.
Not saying we'll need
a miracle to catch up,
but I'd start praying now.
Oh, no, here's Portwenn,
coming up slowly.
But you know what they say:
"Slowly, slowly,
catchy boaty."
(Louisa)
Oh, do they?
(chuckles)
Um, hello.
Can you all hear me?
I just wanted to, well,
to thank you all
for coming, really,
and to say how much
we appreciate
your continued support,
year after year.
(Joe)
Uh, Louisa,
this isn't on the schedule.
(Louisa)
Yeah, just a minute, Joe.
I remember when I first saw
this race as a child,
and then later as a teacher
and now, as headmistress.
And it's always been
my favorite day
of the school year.
Although I've secretly
always wanted
to join
the fishermen's choir!
But now at least today I finally
get to wear the outfit!
(cheering)
Which is fitting
as this year is gonna be
my last year
here at Portwenn school.
(murmuring)
-Hey!
-Do you mind?
(Louisa)
...trying to decide,
and even this morning,
I wasn't sure if I could
go through with this.
I know it's been
a difficult decision
as it's been
such a privilege
getting to know your children
and watching them grow
and making their brave
new steps into the world.
(Becky)
Look out!
(Bert)
Agh!
(Louisa)
Well, I think it's time
for me to do the same.
(Joe)
Don't go anywhere.
Oh, Joe.
-Not you.
-Oh, right.
(Joe)
Right, move.
-Out of my way.
-So...
-Out of the way.
-What I've learnt
from all of you
parents and children is--
is that...
Don't worry, I'll put it
all in the newsletter.
-Got a situation here, Doc.
-Hang on a minute!
I'm the one in pain here.
The car almost
went over my foot.
(Martin)
I told you to get some rest
and stay at home,
and I told you
to stop driving.
(Graham)
I have not been drinking.
(Joe)
He's clearly
under the influence.
I'm gonna get my breathalyzer.
Doc, I have followed him
all night, all day.
He hasn't blinked
without me seeing it.
I've tasted every drink
he's had.
I won't even let him go
to the bathroom alone.
-It's driving me crazy.
-He cannot have been drinking.
(Graham)
Exactly.
(belches)
(Martin)
Well, his blood test
showed the presence of alcohol,
but if you're
absolutely certain,
there might be
another explanation.
(Joe)
I need you to blow into this
until I tell you to stop.
(Martin)
Uh, no, don't bother.
He'd probably fail it,
but that doesn't
necessarily mean
he's been drinking.
You could have
auto-brewery syndrome.
I've never actually
come across it myself,
but fermentation in the gut
leads to ethanol production.
-Say again.
-You'd have to undergo
monitored tests
in hospital,
but if they confirm
the presence
of too much yeast
inside you,
and you haven't been drinking,
then your body
may well be brewing
its own alcohol supply
in your stomach.
(Graham)
So what you're saying is,
basically my body is a brewery?
(Martin)
Yes, that's exactly
what I am saying.
(Graham)
Thanks, Doc.
(Martin)
Come and see me tomorrow.
(Mel)
Thank you.
-Come on.
-Is that my car?
(Mel)
Oh, don't worry about it,
Louisa.
I'll send one of the boys
down to fix it
and then I'll deliver it
to you tomorrow, promise.
(Graham)
Oh, she will.
-She's just amazing.
-Oh!
Oh, God,
you smell terrible
but you do talk lovely.
(Joe)
So you're saying
he's not been drinking
-but he's drunk.
-Yes.
(Joe)
I need more information.
(Martin)
It's the gastrointestinal
organism
saccharomyces cerevisiae.
It's been identified
as a yeast pathogen.
(Joe)
That's too much information.
Oh! The boats.
♪
(rower)
Ease off both sides!
(rowers communicating)
(rowers)
One, two,
three, four.
♪
(rower)
On two!
Give me a big ten!
One, two,
three, four.
(Morwenna)
Come on!
-Yes!
-Come on, we're doing well.
-Come on.
-Come on!
(rower)
Nine, ten.
(grunts)
(breathes heavily)
(tense music)
(rower)
Alice! Hang on!
Stop rowing,
stop rowing.
-Man down!
-Here, lift her up.
-Come on!
(Al)
Mor, I think
something's happened.
-Ignore them!
-What, seriously?
(Samantha)
Guys, I think that girl Alice
has collapsed.
(chatter)
-Steady her.
-Quickly, pull them in.
-What?
-Plenty of wellie.
-Maybe we should stop.
-We're winning!
They wouldn't turn 'round
for us.
(Ellie)
Come on, Morwenna!
(Al)
Yeah, Mor.
(Joe)
And Portwenn are in the lead!
(cheering)
We are watching history
in the making here.
-Come on!
-No. Turn around.
-We're helping.
-Yeah.
-Head to their boat!
-Around!
(Caitlin)
Starboard! Port!
I mean port!
Over there!
(Joe)
But now they are
going backwards.
Why are they
going backwards?
Oh.
There's a man down
in the Port Carran team.
Or should I say, woman down?
Yes, I should.
It's a woman.
Doc, it's an emergency.
♪
-Hold up.
-No, bring her 'round.
(Morwenna)
Throw us a rope
and we'll tow you in!
♪
(Martin)
Put her down here.
-Is she breathing?
-I don't know.
(Martin)
Hello.
Can you hear me?
Not you.
-Don't you touch me!
-What's wrong with her, Doc?
(Martin)
I think she's got
a delayed concussion.
(Alice)
Concussion?
Because of yesterday,
what you did to me?
(Martin)
No, because you ignored
my instruction
to go to bed and rest.
(Alice)
I don't want to hear
any more from you.
-Linda, Michelle, help me up.
-Look, you really need
to let me
examine you properly.
-No!
-All right.
Well, take her to a hospital
and make sure
she gets a CT scan.
(Alice)
Go away!
I can't talk to you.
(blows whistle)
(Joe)
Listen up!
Seeing as
the Port Carran team
have walked away
without acknowledging me,
I am disqualifying them
for flagrant disregard
of the umpire.
-That seems a bit harsh, Joe.
-Shush, Morwenna.
-He's saying we've won.
-Yeah, but we don't want
to just win by default.
(Ellie)
Maybe Dad'll be so happy
he'll let me off fish duty.
(Bert)
No, no, no, no, no,
you can't do this.
(Joe)
I'm the umpire.
I can do that.
(Bert)
Then I would like
to make a formal protest.
(Al)
Dad, you're only protesting
'cause you're gonna lose
-a lot of money on this.
-'Cause I believe
in proper rules
and regulations.
Otherwise it's just anarchy.
(blows whistle)
(Joe)
My official decision
is victory to Portwenn.
(cheering)
Morwenna, as team captain,
do you formally accept?
(Morwenna)
Yeah, I suppose so.
(cheering)
(Joe)
Portwenn it is.
(Eric)
I put 30 quid on Portwenn.
I'm gonna get my Ellie
something nice.
Time to pay up.
(Bert)
I wish I had your luck, Eric.
(chuckles)
-I want my money too.
-Come on!
-No, no.
-You need someone
to look after you.
Shift!
Out of the way!
(Louisa)
Then I told everyone
I was leaving,
so there's no going back now.
(Martin)
Well, that's good.
That's good, isn't it?
And you're still sure
you've made the right decision?
(Louisa)
It's a bit late
to ask that now, isn't it?
No, of course I'm not sure.
But that's what makes it
exciting, I suppose.
You know, the risk.
I mean, yes,
I'd be worried
if you decided
to stop being a doctor.
But things don't have to stay
the same forever, do they?
Do you think your fainting
had anything to do
with my circumstances changing?
(Martin)
No, I don't think so.
(Louisa)
Yes, 'cause you do like
a controlled environment,
-don't you?
-Louisa,
you've only just
started this course.
Please don't use me
as a test case.
(Louisa)
I'm simply
gathering a picture
of your symptoms,
Martin, that's all.
-Hello.
-Hi, Chris.
-Did you come for the race?
-What?
Oh, no, no, no,
I missed all that.
Actually, I'm--
I'm here on business.
Look, perhaps
we could have a talk
in private somewhere, hm?
(Louisa)
Sure, yeah, you carry on.
I've got to get
this little one some food.
Come in for a cup of tea
before you go.
-Please.
-Oh, right.
-What is it?
-Um, yes.
Uh, right,
well, to the point.
Um, I'm afraid
you're in trouble, Martin.
There's a patient.
I tried to talk to her,
I tried to persuade her
not to make a complaint,
but she'd already got
the powers that be involved.
Martin,
she wants you struck off.
-"She" being?
-Alice Taylor.
I believe you drained her cyst?
(Martin)
Her Baker's cyst, yes.
I treated her successfully.
(Chris)
But the patient passed out
and she's claiming
you did as well.
Is that--is that true?
Normally, I could
make this disappear.
But it seems Alice Taylor
is a solicitor.
She made an almighty fuss,
which is how she's got
this moving so quickly.
(Martin)
What exactly is she saying?
(Chris)
You're accused of being
too ill to work safely.
Look, it could be serious.
If your phobia is out of control
and you really can't cope--
(Martin)
No, nothing is out of control.
The woman was suffering
from concussion.
She didn't know
what she was saying.
She wouldn't let me help her
when she collapsed on her boat.
(Chris)
Well, she collapsed again
and you tried to help her?
(Martin)
Yes, of course I did,
that's what I do,
-I'm a doctor.
-Well, you need to stay away
from her
till this is sorted out.
-I certainly will.
-In fact, you need
to stay away from all patients.
(soft music)
(Martin)
What do you mean?
(Chris)
Martin.
I hate to do this, but until
this complaint's been dealt with
you need
to stop practicing.
♪
(Martin)
Are you suspending me?
(Chris)
No, I'm advising you.
Close the surgery
until further notice.
♪
I'll call you tomorrow.
Sorry.
♪
(whimpers)
(theme music)
♪
(soft music)
(bright music)
(upbeat musisic)
(female)
Action!
♪
(laughing)
(male)
Hello.
♪
(Louisa)
How was the emergency?
(Dr. Martin)
Some stupid fisherman
caught his hand in a winch.
Everything was shot on film
when we started doing this
and we always got
lots of compliments
about how it looked.
-So we don't need the dog?
-No, no, we're having the dog.
(Martin Clunes)
Quite Luddite, really,
but that's how I learned
and that's how
we've always done it.
And I love film,
I love the discipline of it.
Most of the crew
love working on it.
Doc Martin is a sort of place
which is a bit lost in time.
Film gives it
a lovely storytelling,
slightly warm period feel.
(Martin Clunes)
The test is whether
somebody's eye
looks like it's made of jelly...
Duck.
Say, "Duck."
...which it always does on film.
It just has a texture
that you have to add
to digital to get,
and when we make
our documentaries
about animals and things,
we usually pepper them
with some footage
of just actuality
of just the animal,
which we shoot
on Super 16 film.
And when people
come at the end and say,
"I love the photography in that,
but that shot of that horse
in the water
and that dingo on the beach,"
and it's the bits
that are shot on film
that seem to speak to them.
(Nick)
We're using 35-mil camera lenses
which are what we call
prime lenses.
They're not a zoom lens,
so you choose
your length of lens
for the size of shot
and you stick with that,
and the only way
of changing that
is to move the camera
towards the artists
or the artists
towards the camera.
There's a lovely depth of field
which means the background
is slightly soft focus,
it's got a lovely warmth to it.
(female)
It's only his first word.
It's not a big deal, really.
(Stuart)
Portwenn, or Port Isaac,
as it really is,
is like a character
in the story.
(uplifting music)
(Martin Clunes)
It's a huge part of it.
It's the whole canvas.
With each director, you get
a different view of Port Isaac
and you just get a slightly
different slant on it.
♪
I love seeing it
sort of reinvented.
♪
We've always believed
that if you're going
to take a picture,
take a nice one.
♪
(Philippa)
And it just adds so much
to every scene that we write,
because you have
this beautiful backdrop.
♪
(female interviewer)
And lots more drones
on Doc Martin.
(Philippa)
Yes. Got me kicking
and screaming
into the 21st century,
'cause last series,
I was really anti them.
It's nice, you know,
we get different angles,
and as long as
it tells the story
rather than just have
a pretty shot.
♪
(Stuart)
Tipping up, going up.
♪
And down maybe.
We're based on
a beautiful Cornish farm...
♪
...which is right by
the North Cornish Coast
facing the Atlantic,
with rolling hills.
It's a working farm.
It's arable and beef cattle.
The producer and directors
and anybody else, really,
who wants to come
and check anything out
can just walk up
to the cutting room.
We're only 30 seconds away
from where
the interior sets are.
So, people can come
if they want to see a shot,
if they want to see anything
for continuity.
It's so easy for everybody
to be on location.
(Philippa)
It's just fantastic
having the editors on-site.
So, I can go into
the edit suite,
I can edit the episodes,
get them up to London,
get them locked
while we're still filming,
and also we can see
at a glance
if we need a pick-up shot,
if we need to reshoot anything.
It just works fantastically
and all the editors
seem quite happy to be here.
When we first started filming
all those years ago,
I used to go up
to the edit suite
and there would be wetsuits
hanging outside, surfboards,
and I thought, "Okay, they got
into the Cornish life here."
(indistinct chatter)
(Martin Clunes)
Nick has been doing it
from day one
and, so, I guess he's had
a hand in sort of inventing,
you know, the editing
style of it.
(Louisa)
At least we don't run the risk
of drowning in the classroom.
(female)
We'll make a sailor
out of you yet.
(Mark)
He so knows the tone
of the show.
It's how you cut out of a shot,
how you link to another scene,
um, and he's very, very clever
with the way he does that.
(child)
Oh, Miss, he's not
feeling very well.
(audio warbles)
(Nigel)
Editing comedy
is very delicate.
(Louisa)
Yeah, nobody panic!
(Nigel)
You just have to find
that perfect rhythm
that throws the audience off
and then brings them back.
It's always--there's always
a sleight of hand with comedy.
"Will you look at this,"
and then you do something
with this hand.
(playful music)
Oh! Oh, no!
(Nick)
It's a sort of comic timing.
It's the way some people
can tell jokes
and other people can't.
Go away!
Disgusting.
Sorry, Doc,
I'll just be a minute.
(Nick)
There's a beat where you cut
to that reaction shot,
and if you get it right,
that's what makes it funny.
I don't think I'll make it
inside, Doc.
No, just go!
Oh, thank you!
No, go inside!
(Nick)
I love working on the show
because I laugh when
I'm cutting shots together.
The actors on Doc Martin
are amazing
because they just put
so much into it
and they are so good
at what they do.
(soft music)
♪
(Philippa)
It is sunny all the time.
It just, uh, well,
it's tricky, actually.
There's a few scenes where
it's a bit cloudy and rainy,
but we just have to have
weather cover all the time,
and this set here is
our standing weather cover set.
So we know if it's gonna be
a horrible, rainy day
and we re-jig
and we come inside.
(Emily)
Good morning, Doctor.
Here are the notes
for your first patient.
(female)
Trevor Dodds!
(Dr. Martin)
Who are you?
(receptionist)
This is Emily.
She's covering for me
for a few days,
-remember?
-No.
We have ways of
making it look sunny.
We can color grade it,
so if it's a bit gray
and overcast,
we can wind a bit
of brightness in,
make it a little bit warmer,
a little bit of orange
which looks like sunlight.
Sound is crucial
at making it flow.
(Nigel)
Sound and music
is often forgotten about,
but it's as important
as anything else,
and you can create
the atmosphere of a scene
with just a single sound effect.
What we do in the dub
is we take all the birds
and seagulls off
and then we add them all
as sound effects.
I'm going, "Well,
we've got them all!"
(tense music)
♪
(Stuart)
Colin Towns has been doing
the music for a long time,
and that's very much a part
of the style of the show.
(soft guitar music)
(Nigel)
The music is what
brings it alive.
cues you to feel stuff,
and it just works so well.
And we've got a great composer,
and he--and usually,
he writes new music
for every single episode.
He sits down and composes
the score for each episode.
(jaunty music)
(male)
That is a lot of whiskey.
(Mark)
We have to hit
absolute specific timing
for our broadcasters.
The scripts have to be
an exact length.
(female)
I'm the new curate.
I didn't realize
we were getting a woman.
(Mark)
Three storylines
that run through each script.
(Dr. Martin)
What on earth are you doing
with that dog?
(Mark)
And to make sure
that they're all tied up
satisfactorily within
the timeframe that we have
while also hitting part breaks
and stuff like that.
It's quite a...
Yeah, it's
an interesting challenge.
It can be incredibly painful.
(rhythmic piano music)
♪
(bright music)
[Glasses clink]
[People speaking indistinctly]
Narrator: Whether you enjoy
gulping them down by the dozen
or eating them carefully
with a fork,
you can find oysters on menus
all over town,
but that wasn't always the case.
Woman: I felt like every
great city has its own
little oyster bar,
and there was really nothing
in D.C. that matched that.
And so, I wanted to
create that here.
My name is Jamie Leeds.
I am the owner and restaurateur
of Hank's Oyster Bar
in Dupont Circle.
Narrator: When Jamie opened
the restaurant in 2005,
she named it
after her father.
Leeds: My dad was
an incredible guy.
He was very happy, joyful,
and loved food.
We used to cook
seafood together.
He died when I was 11.
When I decided to open Hank's,
I thought, "What a perfect name
and a nice homage to him."
[People speaking indistinctly]
Not only do we buy from
around the country,
but we also have
our own local oysters
that you can only get here.
Originally, one of the
farmers just walked in
and shucked his oysters
right in front of me.
I tasted it, and it was
a great oyster.
I said, "OK, you're in."
Woman: My first
oyster was here.
I used to put
a little Tabasco
and maybe a saltine
cracker or something,
but now I just
shuck 'em and eat 'em.
She doesn't like
the cocktail sauce,
so we get one side
of horseradish
and one with cocktail
sauce and horseradish.
Makes the
relationship work.
Ha ha!
Bruce Springsteen:
♪ Got a wife and kids
in Baltimore, Jack... ♪
Narrator: Jamie's urban
beach food menu includes
more than just oysters.
Leeds: We have a full
seafood menu.
I wanted to be able to offer
a non-seafood option as well.
Sunday night is
fried chicken night.
That's a big night.
They've got the small plates,
the large plates and specials,
so I'm trying something new
tonight, which is the salmon.
Everything you get here
is just amazing.
so that's why I love
this place so much.
Springsteen:
♪ ...heart ♪
♪ Everybody's got a... ♪
Narrator: To learn more
about "Neighborhood Eats,"
visit WETA.org.