♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> AND I ASK YOU A PERSONAL
QUESTION?
>> OKAY.
>> TELL ME SOMETHING GOOD.
>> THAT'S NOT A QUESTION.
>> HEY.
>> WHAT?
>> I JUST WANTED TO TAKE ANOTHER
LOOK AT YOU.
♪ ♪
>> HERE'S WHAT WE ARE GOING TO
DO, WE'RE GOING TO DO THAT AFTER
OSCAR SHOW THAT YOU LOVE.
>> I CAN'T DO THAT, I'VE BEEN UP
ALL NIGHT AND I THINK I'M STILL
DRUNK.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> NOW, RYAN, PLEASE, IT'S NOT
FUNNY.
>> ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS TRUST
ME, THAT'S ALL YOU'VE GOT TO DO.
♪ ♪
♪♪ WE ARE FAR FROM THE SHALLOW
NOW ♪♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Announcer: IT'S "LIVE WITH
KELLY AND RYAN"'S AFTER OSCAR
SHOW.
TODAY, RYAN IS ON THE RED CARPET
AND KELLY IS BACKSTAGE WITH ALL
THE HOTTEST ARTIST, INCLUDING
MELISSA McCARTHY, SPIKE LEE,
AND MICHAEL B JORDAN.
PLUS, WE TALKED LAST NIGHT'S BIG
WINNERS REGINA KING, ROBBIE
MALIK, MAHERSHALA ALI AND A
PERFORMANCE FROM SPEED
BEBE REXHA.
ALL NEXT ON "LIVE!"
AND NOW, HERE ARE KELLY RIPA AND
RYAN SEACREST!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ryan: GOOD MORNING,
THANK YOU.
>> Kelly: ALL UP THERE.
IT'S SO NICE.
THANK YOU.
THAT'S VERY KIND.
>> Ryan: WELCOME.
IT IS MONDAY, FOR BERRY 25TH,
2019 LIVE FROM THE DOLBY THEATRE
STAGE WHERE THE OSCARS TOOK
PLACE LAST NIGHT.
>> Kelly: RIGHT ON THIS VERY
STAGE.
>> Ryan: IN WATCHING THAT
PIECE YOU JUST SAW EVEN LAST
NIGHT WHEN LADY GAGA WAS SINGING
IT, I SAW YOUR FACE.
>> Kelly: I AM SORRY ABOUT
THAT.
I'D LIKE TO APOLOGIZE TO
LADY GAGA FOR ANY HARM I MAY
HAVE CAUSED HER CAREER.
>> Ryan: YOU WERE REMARKABLE.
>> Kelly: WHAT'S SO FUNNY IS
NOW I THINK I SOUND LIKE THAT.
>> Ryan: AND I THINK I LOOK
LIKE BRADLEY COOPER.
WE WHEN WE CAN ALL AGREE THAT
YOU KIND OF DO.
>> Ryan: I LOOK LIKE THE
CAVEMAN FROM THE GEICO
COMMERCIAL WITH MY BEARD.
IT WAS A VERY FAKE BEARD.
>> Kelly: I DON'T THINK SO, I
THINK YOU ROCKED IT AND EVEN
THOUGH THEY DID NOT USE RYAN'S
SINGING IN THE PIECE, YOU'RE A
REALLY GOOD SINGER AND I JUST
WANT TO PUT THAT OUT THERE.
>> Ryan: THAT WASN'T MY
SINGING?
YOU TOLD ME THAT WAS MY SINGING.
>> Kelly: HE IS NERVOUS, OKAY?
SO THERE WERE SO MANY AMAZING
MOMENTS LAST NIGHT.
WONDER FOR SURE, EVERYBODY STOP
AT THE PERFORMANCE, THE OPENING
PERFORMANCE BY QUEEN.
AM I RIGHT?
>> Ryan: I LOVED THAT THE SHOW
STARTED IMMEDIATELY WITH A
PERFORMANCE.
TAKE A LOOK.
♪♪ WE WILL, WE WILL ROCK YOU ♪
♪ WE WILL, WE WILL ROCK YOU ♪
♪ WE WILL, WE WILL ROCK YOU ♪♪
>> Kelly: YOU KNOW WHAT'S
INTERESTING?
COULDN'T YOU TELL WHO WAS A
NOMINEE AND HE WAS JUST THERE TO
HAVE FUN JUST BY LOOKING?
SOME PEOPLE WERE WALKING OUT AND
SOME PEOPLE WERE LIKE OKAY.
I'M NERVOUS.
>> Ryan: I TALKED TO ADAM
BEFORE THE SHOW ON THE
RED CARPET, AND HE WAS SO
EXCITED TO BE DOING THAT AND HE
SAID IT'S REALLY COOL TO SEE HER
FOR THE FIRST TIME, I GOT
INVITED TO EVERY SINGLE PARTY.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
OPEN THE OSCARS.
AND HOW ABOUT THAT PERFORMANCE
BY OSCAR-WINNER LADY GAGA AND
BRADLEY COOPER, THEY WERE
FANTASTIC.
♪ ♪
♪♪ I'M OFF THE DEEP END, WATCH
AS I DAVID ♪
♪ CRASHED THROUGH THE SURFACE,
WHERE THEY CAN'T HURT US ♪
♪ WE ARE FAR FROM THE SHALLOW
NOW ♪♪
>> Ryan: I JUST WANT TO TAKE
ANOTHER LOOK AT YOU.
THAT WAS AN INTIMATE PERFORMANC
PERFORMANCE.
>> Kelly: IT LOT OF CHATTER.
>> Ryan: I WAS TOLD THAT
BRADLEY CHOREOGRAPHED THAT.
THAT WAS HIS DESIGN TO GET UP
AND COME OUT OF THE AUDIENCE AND
COME AROUND AND SIT NEXT TO HER.
>> Kelly: NO KIDDING.
I WOULD HAVE SAID YOU KNOW HOW
HARD IT IS TO WALK IN HEELS AND
A BALL GOWN UPSTAGE?
SHE SAID OKAY, LET'S DO IT.
>> Ryan: AND PLAYED AND SANG.
IT'S FUNNY BECAUSE I WAS INSIDE
RIGHT HERE RIGHT AT THE TOP OF
THE SHOW AND I DIDN'T HAVE A
TICKET, SO AS SOON AS I SAID
QUEEN IS COMING UP NEXT.
THEY SAID WE WILL ESCORT YOU OU
OUT.
SO I GET IN THE CAR AND I'M
LEAVING AND IT'S ONE MINUTE
AFTER THE TOP OF THE HOUR AND MY
WINDOW IS DOWN AND THERE IS
L.A.P.D. OFFICERS ON THE CORNER
AND THEY SAY HEY, WE WATCH YOU
AND KELLY, WE'LL SEE YOU IN THE
MORNING.
YOU'RE GOING THE WRONG WAY.
THE OSCARS ARE THAT WAY.
I SAID I'M GOING HOME BECAUSE I
ORDERED ENCHILADAS ON POST MATES
AND MY FAVORITE PIZZA.
STAY WHEN HE DID ORDER
ENCHILADAS ON POST MATES.
>> Ryan: I WATCH AT HOME LIKE
EVERYBODY ELSE WITH ENCHILADAS
AND PIZZA.
WE WENT I WATCHED THE BACKS OF A
GROUP OF PRODUCERS HEADS IN
FRONT OF THE TELEVISION SO TRULS
CAME AROUND THE CORNER, I HAD
NO IDEA WHO WAS COMING AROUND
THE CORNER.
IT WAS LIKE A SURPRISE TO ME
BECAUSE I GOT TO SEE VERY
LITTLE.
SO I ALWAYS SEE THE MOST OF THE
ACADEMY AWARDS WHEN WE DO THIS
SHOW HERE BECAUSE WE SHOW CLIPS
FROM THE ACADEMY AWARDS.
>> Ryan: YOU AND MARK LAST
NIGHT LOOKED OUTSTANDING ON THE
CARPET, I JUST WANT TO SAY.
AND I KNOW I SAY THAT'S ALL THE
TIME, I LOVE TO SEE YOU BOTH
TOGETHER AND I LOVE YOUR
HAPPINESS TOGETHER.
>> Kelly: WE HAVE A LOT OF FUN
TOGETHER AND HE WAS REALLY FUNNY
BECAUSE I JUST TOLD HIM WE WERE
GOING, JUST GOING TO RUN OUT
REAL QUICK AND TALK TO RYAN REAL
QUICK BECAUSE HE AND I ARE
BOTH -- WE ARE NOT BIG
RED CARPET PEOPLE.
IT MAKES US UNCOMFORTABLE TO
HAVE OUR PICTURES TAKEN IN
GENERAL AND I KNOW WE WENT TO
THE WRONG BUSINESS, BUT STILL.
SO WE HAVE TO RUN DOWN TO RYAN
BUT DIDN'T SAY WE ARE IN A
DIFFERENT POSITION THIS YEAR SO
WE HAD TO RUN DOWN PAST THE
PHOTOGRAPHERS AND SO WE ARE
WALKING AND ALL OF A SUDDEN, HE
TURNS AROUND AND LOOKS AT ME AND
GOES A BOY, IT'S A LOT FARTHER
THIS YEAR, ISN'T IT?
IT'S A LOT FARTHER.
AND WE WALK OUT AND THERE WERE
PHOTOGRAPHERS THERE.
WHAT PART IS THIS?
RYAN IS JUST ON THE OTHER SIDE.
>> Ryan: JUST 100 YARDS AWAY.
FOR THE LAST 14 YEARS, I'VE BEEN
ON THE RED CARPET SHOW ASKING
ALL THE A-LIST MOVIE STARS HOW
THEY PREPARE FOR HOLLYWOOD'S
BIGGEST NIGHT.
THIS YEAR, ALSO GIVING YOU AN
EXCLUSIVE LOOK AT HOW I ATTEMPT
TO PREPARE.
TAKE A LOOK.
TESTING ONE, TWO, THREE, CHECK,
CHECK, CHECK, ONE, TWO, THREE.
HELLO, AMERICA.
WELCOME TO LIVE FROM THE
RED CARPET, THE 91ST
ACADEMY AWARDS.
WE ARE HERE ON THE RED CARPET AT
THE OSCARS REHEARSING FOR E.
HI, GIULIANA.
HOW DID WE DO?
I'M NOT GIVING IT ALL THE WAY,
GET OUT OF HERE.
SAVE SOME FOR THE SHOW.
SPIKE LEE, WHEN HE FOUND OUT HE
GOT NOMINATED.
HE'S EXCITED.
I'M EXCITED TO TALK TO HIM.
THAT'S GREAT.
WELCOME TO OSCAR CLASS.
THIS IS ME STUDYING QUESTIONS SO
I HAVE SOMETHING TO ASK.
WE ARE GOING TO BE HERE ALL
NIGHT STUDYING QUESTIONS FOR ALL
THE OSCAR STARS SO I WILL SEE
YOU FIRST THING IN THE MORNING.
♪ ♪
[HUMMING]
ARE YOU EXCITED FOR BREAKFAST?
I'M EXCITED FOR THAT BREAKFAST.
IT'S OSCAR SUNDAY.
CALF AND NATION.
IT'S YOUR CALIFORNIA FANTASY.
FRESH CITRUS.
I DON'T WANT TO BE RECOGNIZED.
IT'S A BIG NIGHT FOR ALL OF THE
STARS THAT ARE THERE, AND IT'S
IN IMPORTANT NIGHT AND YOU WANT
TO MAKE THEM FEEL GOOD TO KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
I'M EXCITED TO SEE REGINA KING
TONIGHT, COULD BE A BIG NIGHT
FOR REGINA KING.
EXCITED TO SEE JASON MOMOA.
WHO WOULDN'T BE?
THEY PUT JENNIFER LOPEZ, BF,
ALEX.
LOOK WHO'S CALLING.
CONNIE SEACREST, MOM.
HELLO?
>> HEY, BUDDY.
IT'S PRETTY WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> SOMETHING IS GOING ON TONIGH
TONIGHT.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE WHAT YOU'RE
WEARING.
>> Ryan: I'M WEARING A TUXEDO.
DON'T WANT TO RUIN IT.
>> PLANE OR WHISKERS?
>> Ryan: YOU HAVE TO TUNE IN
TO FIND OUT.
>> I THINK WE ARE DOING A PIZZA
NIGHT.
>> Ryan: SPEAKING MY LANGUAGE.
WHAT KIND OF PIZZA?
>> MR. SEACREST LIKES THE
MARGARITA.
WE WANTED TO WISH YOU LUCK.
>> Ryan: TALK TO YOU LATER,
LOVE YOU, BYE.
SEND FOOD PICKS, BYE.
>> Kelly: HELLO?
>> Ryan: I'M ON MY WAY.
I LOVE YOU JUST      REST CHOIC.
>> Kelly: GOOD, THANK YOU.
ULTIMATELY, I ASKED MY MOM AND
MY DAD.
>> Ryan: THAT'S SO FUNNY, THEY
HAVE BIG INFLUENCES ON A STILL
TO THIS DAY.
WE ARE CHECKING IN.
GELMAN, YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE.
COMPLIMENTS OF THE HOLLYWOOD
HOTEL.
YOU DIDN'T.
A LITTLE HAIRCUT.
FRINGE BENEFITS.
WE WILL SEE YOU OUT THERE ON THE
RED CARPET WITH ALL THE STARS.
♪ ♪
I AM HERE ON THE OSCARS
RED CARPET AT MY STATION WHERE
WE HAVE BEEN FOR OVER A DECADE
HOSTING THE RED CARPET SHOW
READY FOR THE STARS TO ARRIVE.
♪ ♪
REGINA'S HERE.
THIS IS KELLY AND RYAN.
>> THE THING THAT I'M BRINGING
IN WITH ME TONIGHT IS THE
OVERWHELMING AMOUNT OF LOVE THAT
I HAVE GOTTEN FROM PEOPLE.
IT'S PRETTY WHAT TIME IS IT?
GOOD TASTE.
>> IF YOU WANT TO TOUCH IT, GO
AHEAD.
>> Ryan: SHE MIGHT HAVE AN
OSCAR AND AN HOUR AND A HALF.
I REMEMBER WATCHING YOU 15 YEARS
AGO WHEN YOU WERE UP ON STAGE
ACCEPTING FIVE YEARS AGO.
FIVE YEARS AGO JUST A CHILD.
THE OFFICE HERE AT THE
RED CARPET, LIVE RIGHT NOW.
GOING TO COMMERCIAL.
THERE IS TOM, MANY YEARS HERE,
MY BROTHER.
THERE IS THE TEAM, MARCO,
CHRISTINE, GELMAN.
THIS IS OUR SPACE RIGHT HERE.
I HEAR KELLY IS COMING BY SOON.
YOU AND QUEEN ARE OPENING THE
ACADEMY AWARDS.
>> IT IS MIND-BLOWING.
I'M SO HONORED TO BE HERE.
DO YOU ARE NO STRANGER TO THIS
VERY THEATER.
>> FOR MANY REASONS.
YOU KNOW THAT.
>> Ryan: I WAS THERE, I
REMEMBER.
>> HOW MANY JOBS DO YOU HAVE?
>> Ryan: I'M LOOKING FOR WORK
ALWAYS.
TAKING OVER THE WORLD, MUSIC AND
FILM.
>> AND JUGGLING.
♪ ♪
>> Ryan: WE ARE GOING FROM E
TO ABC.
>> MADE HIS WAY UP TO OUR STAGE,
MY FRIEND RYAN SEACREST.
>> Ryan: HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M GREAT, HOW ARE YOU?
YOU MADE IT OVER HERE.
>> Ryan: LOOK WHO I FOUND,
MARK CONSUELOS AND A FAMILIAR
FACE, KELLY RIPA.
>> I LOVE YOUR JACKET.
>> Ryan: YOU GUYS LOOK SO
STUNNING TOGETHER, TERRIFIC.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I'M VERY EXCITED TO TAKE OUR
SHOW INSIDE THE DOLBY THEATRE.
>> Ryan: GREAT TO SEE YOU
BOTH, YOU LOOK AMAZING TONIGHT.
>> SO DO YOU, THANK YOU.
>> Ryan: HERE ON AWARDS WALK
HEADING INTO THE DOLBY THEATRE,
THE STARS AS YOU CAN SEE OR
ABOUT TO TAKE THEIR SEATS,
CHECKING THEIR TEXT MESSAGES FOR
ONE FINAL TIME BEFORE IT ALL
BEGINS.
FOR HOLLYWOOD'S BIGGEST NIGHT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: BY THE WAY, JUST
WANT TO POINT OUT HE REALLY DID
LIVE UP TO YOUR HARDEST WORKING
MAN IN SHOW BUSINESS TITLE.
YOU REALLY DO.
YOU ALWAYS IMPRESSED ME WITH HOW
YOU DO YOUR JOB SO SEAMLESSLY.
>> Ryan: I BROUGHT YOU A
LITTLE SOMETHING BEFORE YOU GET
TO THE ROSES.
YOU'VE ALWAYS TALKED ABOUT
HAVING A CITRUS TREE.
THIS IS THE SEED TO YOUR FUTURE.
>> Kelly: THANK YOU SO MUCH, I
APPRECIATE IT.
AND I MADE YOU THIS BACKSTAGE.
>> Ryan: I NOTICED THAT YOU
JUST SMELL THE ROSES, CAN YOU
SHOW AMERICA WHAT YOU ARE
SNIFFING?
SPEAK WHAT I WANTED TO TAKE A
SNIFF.
IT IS SENT FREE, BUT THERE WERE
40,000 RED ROSES FROM ECUADOR
ONSET.
THEY DEHYDRATED THEM WITH THIS
PROCESS, THEY REMOVE ALL OF THE
MOISTURE AND WATER OUT OF THEM
AND THEN THEY REHYDRATE THEM
WITH SOME SORT OF SPECIAL OIL
WAS IN THE THESE WILL LIVE FOR A
YEAR.
>> Ryan: UNTIL NEXT
VALENTINE'S DAY.
>> Kelly: LONGER THAN THAT.
>> Ryan: LETS GRAB SOME OF
THESE FOR NEXT YEAR.
WE HAVE A BIG SHOW FOR YOU
TODAY, OSCAR WINNER RAMI MALEK
TALKS ABOUT HIS BEST ACTOR WHEN
WITH YOU.
THAT'S EXCITING.
>> Kelly: THAT WAS AN EXCITING
MOMENT, THAT SPEECH HE GAVE,
JUST GORGEOUS.
AND BEBE REXHA IS PERFORMING HER
NEW HIT "LAST HURRAH" LIVE FOR
THE FIRST TIME RIGHT HERE.
>> Ryan: PEOPLES EDITOR IN
CHIEF ARE HERE WITH A ROUND UP
OF LAST NIGHT'S BIG MOMENTS AND
ALSO THE HOTTEST FASHIONS.
WHEN YOU ARE SPORTING THE
HOTTEST FASHIONS RIGHT NOW.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
>> Ryan: I'VE USED THIS
BEFORE.
>> Kelly: NOTHING LIKE A GOOD
REPEAT.
AND COMING UP NEXT, GOING TO SEE
WHAT HAPPENED WHEN I WAS
BACKSTAGE AND TALKING WITH ALL
THE BIG STARS AND ALL THE BIG
WINNERS AFTER THEY LEFT THE
OSCAR STAGE.
>> Ryan: LIVE FROM THE DOLBY
IN HOLLYWOOD.
>> Announcer: STILL AHEAD ON
"LIVE," BEBE REXHA PERFORMS HER
NEW HIT LIVE FOR THE VERY FIRST
TIME.
WE WILL TALK WITH ACADEMY AWARD
WINNER RAMI MALEK AND GIVE YOU
THE LOWDOWN ON ALL THE NIGHTS
BIG MOMENTS ON HOTTEST FASHIONS.
COMING UP NEXT, KELLY TAKES US
BACKSTAGE AT THE OSCARS WHEN SHE
TALKS TO ALL THE NIGHT'S BIGGEST
STARS.
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ryan: WELCOME BACK.
>> Kelly: WE WERE JUST
WATCHING THAT.
WHY ARE WE SHOWING MOVIE
POSTERS?
DIDN'T MAKE THE CONNECTION.
UNTIL THE LAST ONE.
>> Ryan: IT'S EARLY.
WE WENT LAST NIGHT, THE OSCARS
WAS FULL OF SURPRISES OF COURSE.
LAUGHS, TEARS, THERE WERE HUGE
WINNERS, AND THEN WHEN THE BIG
MOMENT HAPPENED, I WAS LUCKY
ENOUGH TO BE BACKSTAGE WITH THEM
TO HELP THEM CELEBRATE.
TAKE A LITTLE LOOK.
HERE WE ARE BACKSTAGE AT THE
OSCARS OR LIKE THEY SAY IN
HOLLYWOOD, LIGHTS, CAMERA,
LIQUORISH.
>> ON THE OSCAR GOES TO
REGINA KING.
HE WENT OH, MY GOSH, LOOK WHO'S
HERE.
YOU JUST HOSTED THE
ACADEMY AWARDS.
I JUST WANT TO SAY ONE THING, DO
YOU REMEMBER WE HAD A
CONVERSATION ABOUT THIS MOMENT
ON OUR SHOW.
AND I KNOW IT'S YOUR FIRST
NOMINATION WHICH I CANNOT
BELIEVE, BUT I'M NOT SURPRISED
THAT YOUR FIRST NOMINATION
RESULTED IN YOUR FIRST WIN.
HOW DOES IT FEEL?
>> I AM VIBRATING RIGHT NOW.
TO HAVE THESE THREE WOMEN, OH,
MY GOD.
THAT WAS A HUGE DEAL.
AND WHAT EVEN MORE AMAZING IS
THIS MORNING, I GET THESE EMAILS
OF QUOTES AND I GOT A QUOTE FROM
AMY POEHLER THIS MORNING THAT
WAS A QUOTE THIS MORNING AND SO
WHEN SHE WALKED OUT, I WAS LIKE
IS THIS A SIGN?
IS THIS A SIGN TO?
AND THE QUOTE WAS SURROUND
YOURSELF WITH PEOPLE THAT
CHALLENGE YOU AND THAT INSPIRE
YOU AND I FEEL LIKE I SUBSCRIBE
TO THAT.
>> Kelly: WHAT DOES IT FEEL
LIKE?
>> IT'S HEAVY.
>> Kelly: YOU WANT ME TO HOLD
IT FOR YOU WHILE YOU WATCH THE
REST OF THE SHOW?
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
YOU LOOK REALLY PRETTY OUT
THERE.
I TOLD YOU, HE IS WEARING A
SCRUNCHY.
WHO ELSE ARE YOU EXCITED ABOUT
TONIGHT?
TO MAKE EVERYONE.
>> Kelly: SPEAKING OF
DRINKING, WOULD YOU LIKE TO
DRINK SOMETHING WHILE YOU'RE
HERE?
YOU WANT A LITTLE LIME?
>> IT'S GOOD WHATEVER.
>> Kelly: DO YOU NEED MORE
THAN THAT BECAUSE YOUR LARGER?
ARE YOU SURE?
>> COULD SNEAK THOSE LITTLE ONES
AND THERE.
IT WASN'T ME, IT WAS KELLY AND
RYAN.
>> Kelly: WHAT WAS THE IDEA
BEHIND YOUR DESIGNS TONIGHT?
WHAT WAS YOUR THOUGHT PROCESS?
>> I THINK WE WERE BOTH THINKING
SUBTLETY.
>> Kelly: THAT'S WHAT'S SO
DIFFERENT ABOUT EACH OF YOU.
HOW DID I NOT KNOW THAT YOU HAD
SO MANY RABBITS.
>> THERE ARE SO MANY RABBITS.
>> Kelly: DO YOU FEEL THAT
GLENN CLOSE MIGHT GET TRIGGERED
WHEN SHE SEES THIS?
>> THERE'S A DOUBLE ENTENDRE.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO
MAHERSHALA ALI.
>> Kelly: TWO WINS, YOU HAVE
THE MAGIC TOUCH FOR SURE.
>> I'VE BEEN VERY FORTUNATE.
>> Kelly: I LOVE THIS MOVIE
AND I HAD SUCH GOOD FEELINGS AND
HIGH HOPES.
I WAS REALLY VERY HOPEFUL THAT
YOU WOULD WIN AGAIN AND I'M SO
HAPPY.
>> THANK YOU, I'M PROUD TO BE A
PART OF IT.
>> Kelly: I WANT TO KNOW, WHAT
WOULD MY DSA AT THE OSCARS?
>> MY FEET HURT.
AND IS THAT CHAMPAGNE?
>> Kelly: I WAS CURIOUS IF YOU
WOULD CONSIDER PLAYING A GAME
WITH ME?
HE MET THE PENS WITH THE GAME
IS.
>> Kelly: FIRST CONCERT.
>> NOT VAN MORRISON.
WAIT, MIGHT'VE BEEN ONE THAT I
SNUCK INTO.
I THINK JAMES TAYLOR.
>> Kelly: HE WATCHES THE SHOW
EVERY DAY.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU REMEMBER
THIS, MICHELLE, YOU ARE NOT
THERE.
WE WERE IN A JAY-Z VIDEO
TOGETHER.
>> WHICH ONE?
THIS IS LIKE THE HOW MANY THINGS
CAN WE NAME.
>> Kelly: LET ME REMEMBER
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN IN SO MANY
JAY-Z VIDEOS.
LET ME THINK ABOUT IT.
CHANGE CLOTHES.
OBVIOUSLY, IT MEANT MORE TO ME
THEN TO YOU, BUT THAT'S OKAY.
>> I ACTUALLY REMEMBER NOW.
>> Kelly: CAN WE SEE THE
ENVELOPE?
>> YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHO IT IS.
ASK ME WHEN I WAS TO SAY.
>> YOU'RE REALLY GOOD, RUNNING
CIRCLES AROUND ME.
>> Kelly: STAY IN YOUR LANE
AND I'LL STAY IN MINE.
IT'S WORKING OUT FOR YOU, IT
REALLY IS.
DO YOU EVER THINK ABOUT BECOMING
A DOCTOR?
>> IN ACTION HERO.
I CAN RUN, I CAN JUMP, I CAN
FIGHT.
WHEN YOU FIT INTO ALL OF IT, I
THINK.
>> AND THE OSCAR GOES TO...
>> SPIKE LEE!
WE WENT OH, MY GOSH, I'M SO
HAPPY FOR YOU.
I AM TRULY HAPPY FOR YOU AND I
HOPE YOU KNOW THE WHOLE ROOM WAS
REALLY HAPPY FOR YOU.
>> I FELT THE LOVE.
>> Kelly: DID YOU KNOW THE
NEXT WON?
>> WE ARE TRYING TO LOSE.
>> Kelly: IT WAS GREAT TO SEE
SPIKE WIN, IT WAS HUGE.
IT WAS A GREAT MOMENT, DON'T YOU
THINK?
YOU ARE A FILM ICON AND NOW YOU
ARE RICH.
>> MY WIFE IS RICH.
>> Kelly: THAT'S OKAY.
SHE HAD GOOD GARTER OF THE
MONEY?
>> SHE'S KILLING IT.
PEOPLE SAY TO ME WHAT'S IN YOUR
WALLET?
MY WIFE'S NAME.
DEEP IN MY POCKET.
♪ ♪
>> Kelly: TEACH ME A MOVIE
PUNCH BECAUSE I WOULD REALLY
LOVE TO MOVIE PUNCH GELMAN.
>> DEPENDS ON WHERE THE CAMERA
IS.
SO I'M GOING TO COME FROM THIS
WAY AND YOU GO THAT WAY.
SLOW MOTION.
I CONTACT IS VERY IMPORTANT.
SO COME HERE.
>> Kelly: AND I HAVE TO SELL
IT, RIGHT?
>> NO, YOU'RE A WOMAN, NO,
NEVER.
WHEN YOU ARE HITTING GELMAN.
>> IN THAT CASE, LET'S DO THIS.
WHEN YOU REALLY HAVE TO SELL IT.
I CONTACT.
YEAH.
WE CAME, WE SAW, WE CELEBRATED
IT.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S HOW THEY
WOULD TOWN WILL EVER BE THE SAM
SAME.
I MISSED IT.
>> Announcer: NEXT, BEST ACTOR
OSCAR WINNER RAMI MALEK.
DEAREST BRITAIN.
WE LOVE YOU.
MAYBE IT'S YOUR BIG HEARTS.
YOUR SENSE OF STYLE.
WELCOME TO BA100.
(BA100,
YOU'RE CLEAR FOR TAKE-OFF).
HOW YOU FOLLOW YOUR OWN PATH.
YOU'VE LED REVOLUTIONS...
OF ALL KINDS.
YET YOU WON'T SHOUT ABOUT IT.
IT'S JUST NOT IN YOUR NATURE.
INSTEAD, YOU'LL
QUIETLY MAKE HISTORY.
CAKE.
BEDS.
POETRY.
TROUBLE.
LOVE! HOPE!
AND RATHER A LOT OF TEA.
THE BEST OF BRITAIN,
FROM THE MOMENT
YOU STEP ON BOARD.
>> Ryan: WE ARE BACK LIVE AT
THE DOLBY.
SO CLARK GABLE, LAURENCE OLIVIE
OLIVIER, JACK NICHOLSON, DENZEL
WASHINGTON, TOM HANKS, ALL
INCREDIBLE ACTORS, ALL
INCREDIBLE OSCAR WINNERS.
LAST NIGHT, A NEW NAME WAS ADDED
TO THAT LIST OF TALENTED MEN,
RAMI MALEK.
SO TERRIFIC AS AN ACTOR AND A
GREAT GUY.
WATCH THIS.
♪ ♪
>> THE OSCAR GOES TO RAMI MALEK.
>> Kelly: I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU
YOU.
I COULD NOT BE HAPPIER.
>> YOU CAN'T BE HAPPIER THAN ME.
WE WENT I'M SURE YOU'RE THE
HAPPIEST BUT WE ARE ALL THE
SECOND HAPPIEST.
WE WATCH THIS MOVIE AND I FELT
LIKE I WAS WATCHING A
DOCUMENTARY, AND I KNOW YOU.
YOU'VE BEEN ON THE SHOW.
WE LOVE HAVING YOU ON OUR SHOW.
AND I HAVE TO TELL YOU AS I WAS
WATCHING YOU GIVE YOUR SPEECH,
IT WAS SO BEAUTIFUL AND I DON'T
KNOW IF YOU NOTICED, BUT THEY
FOUND YOUR MOM.
THEY FOUND YOUR MOM IN THE
AUDIENCE.
>> Rami: OH, MY GOD, .
MY MOM IS IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
I LOVE YOU, I LOVE YOU, LADY.
MY FAMILY, THANK YOU FOR ALL OF
THIS.
I NEVER TALK ABOUT PERSONAL
STUFF.
I WILL SAY THIS TODAY.
MY MOM WAS PREGNANT WITH MY
BROTHER AND I, I'M A TWIN AND AS
A KID, SHE TOOK THREE BUSES TO
GET TO WORK, THREE DIFFERENT
BUSES SO THAT SHE COULD
EVENTUALLY GIVE US A BETTER LIFE
WITH MY DAD AND THEY WORKED SO
HARD TO TELL US TO DO SOMETHING
SPECIAL, BE SOMETHING SPECIAL NO
MATTER WHAT IT WAS, SO TO SHARE
THIS WITH HER WAS THE GREATEST
MOMENT I COULD HAVE ASKED FOR.
I'VE GOT TO SAY, SOMEHOW THE WAY
SHE RAISED ME INTRODUCED ME TO
SOME GOOD PEOPLE AND I DIDN'T
WANT TO GIVE A LIST OF NAMES OUT
THERE BUT THE PEOPLE WHO HAVE
SUPPORTED ME, THEY ARE RIGHT
HERE BEHIND THIS CAMERA, THERE
IS AN AGENT THAT'S BEEN WITH ME
FOR SO LONG AS AN ACTOR WHO IS
RIGHT THERE.
TO BE WHERE IS DOUG?
COME HERE.
IF JUST FOR A SECOND.
WHAT AN AGENT.
>> Rami: THAT IS BEN CURTIS
THAT YOU JUST SAW.
CYNTHIA PATTON.
AND DAVID WEBER, THESE GUYS, WE
DON'T GET TO DO THIS WITHOUT AN
ARMY BEHIND US.
WE ARE SO PRIVILEGED AND SO
LUCKY SO IT'S ONE TYPE OF
FAMILY, IT'S ANOTHER TYPE OF
FAMILY, AND I'VE BEEN THINKING
FREDDIE MERCURY THROUGHOUT THIS
PROCESS.
I WANTED TO THANK QUEEN BECAUSE
JUST AN INTEGRAL PART OF THAT
BAND.
I AM NOT THE LEAD SINGER.
I AM NOT THE LEADER OF THE BAND,
JUST THE LEAD SINGER AND I
THOUGHT THAT WAS SO BEAUTIFUL
THAT HE COULD MAKE IT SO
COLLABORATIVE, BUT RIGHT NOW I
WILL GIVE IT TO YOU, MY MAN.
I MAY NOT HAVE BEEN THE OBVIOUS
CHOICE, BUT I GUESS IT WORKED
OUT.
>> Kelly: THIS IS YOUR FIRST
OSCAR NOMINATION, YOUR FIRST
WHEN, WHEN THEY CALLED YOUR
NAME, TAKE ME INTO YOUR BRAIN.
WHAT WAS THE FIRST THING THAT
POPPED INTO YOUR BRAIN?
THE VERY FIRST THOUGHT, IF YOU
CAN REMEMBER.
>> Rami: I'LL TELL YOU THIS.
I START RUNNING EVERYBODY ELSE'S
NAME THAT'S NOMINATED IN MY HEAD
SO I CAN JUST ANTICIPATE THAT
THAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
SO I'M GOING TO BRADLEY,
CHRISTIAN, WILLEM AND I JUST
KEEP REPEATING THEM OVER AND
OVER AGAIN.
I JUST KNOW I'M GOING TO CLAP
FOR ANYONE BECAUSE I THINK I WAS
PART OF A GROUP OF ACTORS THAT
I'VE ADMIRED FOR SO MANY YEARS.
THOSE GUYS ALL DESERVE TO WIN
AND WHEN IT HITS YOU THAT SEE IS
YOU, YOU MUSTER UP THE ENERGY TO
PUT A COHESIVE SENTENCE AND THE
FIRST THING TO COME TO YOUR MIND
IS THANK MOM, I THINK THE PEOPLE
WHO HELPED GET YOU HERE AND JUST
SPEAK ABOUT SOMETHING THAT MEANS
SO MUCH TO YOU.
PART OF MY STORY IS BEING
WRITTEN RIGHT NOW, AND I COULD
NOT BE MORE GRATEFUL TO EACH AND
EVERY ONE OF YOU AND EVERYONE
WHO BELIEVED IN ME FOR THIS
MOMENT.
IT IS SOMETHING I WILL TREASURE
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
JUST GIVE IT YOUR ALL, SO
THANK YOU FOR ALWAYS HAVING MY
BACK.
>> Kelly: ALWAYS, THANK YOU.
>> Rami: I AM BLESSED, I COULD
NOT BE MORE THANKFUL.
>> Kelly: YOU DESERVE IT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Announcer: UP NEXT,
BEBE REXHA DEBUTS HER NEW SONG.
LIFE HAS PARTNERED WITH NATIVE
FOR THE PREDICT THE WINNER'S
BALLOT CONTEST.
TUNE IN THIS WEEK WHEN WE REVEAL
THE GRAND PRIZE WINNER.
DON'T SWEAT THE SMALL STUFF WITH
THE NATIVE DEODORANT.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
>> Ryan: BEBE REXHA IS A
GRAMMY NOMINATED SINGER AND
SONGWRITER, THIS IS HER
TELEVISION DEBUT OF HER NEW HIT
SONG "LAST HURRAH."
THEY DO'S AND GENTLEMEN, THE ONE
AND ONLY BEBE REXHA.
♪ ♪
♪♪ I'M DONE WITH THE DRINKING,
I'M DONE WITH THE SMOKING ♪
♪ I'M DONE WITH THE PLAYING, I'M
DONE WITH THE JOKING ♪
♪ I'M DONE WITH THE LADIES, I'M
DONE WITH THE FELLAS ♪
♪ JUST SAYIN'  ♪
♪ FAREWELL TEQUILA, SO LONG
MARGARITA ♪
♪ AND LADY SATIVA, I HATE TO
LEAVE YA ♪
♪ DON'T WANT THE PRESSURE, I
DON'T NEED A LECTURE ♪
♪ NO, THANK YOU, HONEY, GOD
BLESS YA ♪
♪ I KNOW I'VE SAID IT ALL
BEFORE ♪
♪ BUT IT WON'T HURT TO DO IT ALL
ONCE MORE ♪
♪ THIS IS MY LAST HURRAH, ONCE I
START ♪
♪ I AIN'T GON' STOP 'TIL I GO
TOO FAR ♪
♪ LAST HURRAH AND IT'S OKAY ♪
♪ MAYBE TOMORROW I WON'T FEEL
THIS PAIN ♪
♪ LAST HURRAH ♪
♪ I'M DONE WITH THE HEARTACHE,
I'M DONE WITH THE DEMONS ♪
♪ CAN'T WAIT TO BE NORMAL, RIGHT
AFTER THIS WEEKEND ♪
♪ I'M DONE WITH THE DRAMA, I'M
FIXING MY KARMA ♪
♪ ONE MORE NIGHT UP YOUR
NIRVANA ♪
♪ I KNOW I'VE SAID IT ALL
BEFORE ♪
♪ BUT IT WON'T HURT TO DO IT ALL
ONCE MORE ♪
♪ THIS IS MY LAST HURRAH, ONCE I
START ♪
♪ I AIN'T GON' STOP 'TIL I GO
TOO FAR ♪
♪ LAST HURRAH AND IT'S OKAY ♪
♪ MAYBE TOMORROW I WON'T FEEL
THIS PAIN ♪
♪ LAST HURRAH ♪
♪ MAYBE I'LL NEVER CHANGE ♪
♪ BUT I'M STILL GLAD I CAME ♪
♪ TRY AGAIN ANOTHER DAY ♪
♪ BUT FOR NOW ♪
♪ THIS IS MY LAST HURRAH, ONCE I
START ♪
♪ I AIN'T GON' STOP 'TIL I GO
TOO FAR ♪
♪ LAST HURRAH AND IT'S OKAY ♪
♪ MAYBE TOMORROW I WON'T FEEL
THIS PAIN ♪
♪ LAST HURRAH ♪
♪ LAST HURRAH ♪♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelly: WOW.
A SPEECH BEBE REXHA!
>> Kelly: THAT WAS AMAZING.
IT INCREDIBLE.
>> Ryan: SUPER TALENTED.
>> WE ARE IN THE OSCAR THEATER.
>> Kelly: YOU DID IT, YOU MADE
THE DAZZLE HAPPEN, THAT WAS
INCREDIBLE.
>> Ryan: BEBE REXHA'S NEW
SINGLE IS AVAILABLE NOW.
WE WENT COMING UP NEXT, OR OSCAR
ROUND UP.
TO STICK.
STICK AROUND.
>> Announcer: IF YOU'D LIKE TO
SEE MORE BEHIND THE SCENES
FOOTAGE FROM OUR TRIP TO
HOLLYWOOD OR MORE INFO ABOUT
ANYTHING YOU SEE ON "LIVE," JUST
GO TO OUR WEB SITE.
>> Announcer: THE DAY AFTER
THE BIGGEST OSCAR PARTY EVER,
KELLY AND RYAN ARE BACK IN NYC.
>> Kelly: YESTERDAY SAID I
NEED TO REST YOUR VOICE.
I'VE GOT TO GO DO THE RADIO
SHOW.
>> Announcer: NEXT "LIVE,"
WHISKEY CAVALIER AND DEREK HOUG
HOUGH.
>> Announcer: LIFE HAS
PARTNERED WITH VISIT BRITAIN AND
BRITISH AIRWAYS FOR THE AFTER
OSCAR SHOW.
TRAVEL FOR THE UNEXPECTED FOR
BREATHTAKING LANDSCAPES TO
UNIQUE EXPERIENCES AND THE
EXCITING FOOD AND DRINK SCENE.
FIND YOUR GREAT BRITAIN.
>> Ryan: WELCOME BACK.
>> Kelly: LAST NIGHT OSCAR
SHOW, INCREDIBLE FASHION, EVEN A
FEW SURPRISES.
HERE TO RECAP THE BIG NIGHT IS
PEOPLE EDITOR IN CHIEF.
WELCOME, THANK YOU FOR WAITING.
JUST TELL US.
>> Ryan: LET'S GET INTO IT.
>> Kelly: WHAT WERE THE BEST
MOMENTS?
>> THE BIGGEST MOMENT I THOUGHT
WAS WHEN GLENN CLOSE DID NOT WIN
FOR BEST ACTRESS.
EVERYBODY SAID, IT WAS LIKE WHEN
LA-LA LAND ONE, BUT DIDN'T WIN.
IT WAS A REAL SHOCK.
BUT THEN OLIVIA COLMAN WON.
AND SHE GAVE ONE OF THE BEST
SPEECHES OF THE NIGHT, SO FUNNY
AND SO SWEET.
THERE SHE IS.
SHE MADE HER HUSBAND CRY THAT
MADE FUN OF HIM FOR IT WHICH WAS
AMAZING.
>> Kelly: THAT'S A SIGN OF A
HEALTHY RELATIONSHIP.
>> THE OTHER GREAT THING ABOUT
LAST NIGHT'S CEREMONY WAS THE
DIVERSITY AMONG THE WINNERS.
NOTABLY, SPIKE LEE, FINALLY WON
AND OSCAR.
>> Kelly: I JUST LOVED HIS
UNABASHED JOY.
>> EXACTLY, HE WAS JOYOUS AND
OUTSPOKEN, JUST FANTASTIC.
THERE IS A WOMAN WHO ACTUALLY
WON FOR PRODUCTION DESIGN FOR
"BLACK PANTHER," SHE IS NOT ONLY
THE FIRST AFRICAN-AMERICAN TO
WIN FOR PRODUCTION DESIGN, SHE'S
THE FIRST AFRICAN-AMERICAN
NOMINATED FOR PRODUCTION DESIGN.
>> Ryan: WE ARE GOING TO TAKE
A BREAK AND COME BACK AND TALK
ABOUT THE HOTTEST FASHIONS OF
THE NIGHT RIGHT AFTER THIS FROM
THE DOLBY THEATRE.
>> Announcer: STILL AHEAD,
FASHION FAVORITES.
DEAREST BRITAIN.
WE LOVE YOU.
MAYBE IT'S YOUR BIG HEARTS.
YOUR SENSE OF STYLE.
WELCOME TO BA100.
(BA100,
YOU'RE CLEAR FOR TAKE-OFF).
HOW YOU FOLLOW YOUR OWN PATH.
YOU'VE LED REVOLUTIONS...
OF ALL KINDS.
YET YOU WON'T SHOUT ABOUT IT.
IT'S JUST NOT IN YOUR NATURE.
INSTEAD, YOU'LL
QUIETLY MAKE HISTORY.
CAKE.
BEDS.
POETRY.
TROUBLE.
LOVE! HOPE!
AND RATHER A LOT OF TEA.
THE BEST OF BRITAIN,
FROM THE MOMENT
YOU STEP ON BOARD.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
50 WELCOME BACK.
LET'S TALK FASHION.
WHAT WERE YOUR FAVORITES FROM
LAST NIGHT?
>> I ALWAYS LOVE EMMA STONE,
VERY AVANT-GARDE LOUIS VUITTON,
SHE HAD JEWELS IN HER HAIR, TOOK
712 HOURS TO MAKE THAT DRESS.
PRETTY GOOD.
CASEY MUSGRAVE'S SPLIT THE
CROWDED LEVEL.
KNOWN FOR THESE CRAZY CREATIONS,
HAUTE COUTURE WITH A LITTLE BIT
OF RUFFLE, LOADS OF RUFFLES ALL
OVER THE RED CARPET.
VERY ELEGANT.
>> THE INTERNET SAID SHE LOOKED
LIKE A LOOFAH.
I DO SHE IS GORGEOUS.
>> SHE WAS THE ONE TO WATCH ON
THAT RED CARPET, ANOTHER VERY
VOLUMINOUS STRESS.
>> Kelly: I LOVE THE
REGINA KING, SHE WAS MY FIRST
FAVORITE BECAUSE I LOVE A WHITE
GOWN, I LOVE THE SLIT AND THE
RUSHING, IT WAS STUNNING.
IT'S BEEN A GREAT CHOICE, MAKE
SURE TO PICK UP A COPY OF
"PEOPLE" MAGAZINE.
GREAT TO SEE YOU EARLY THIS
MORNING.
NEXT UP, WHICH MEMBER OF OUR
STUDIO AUDIENCE WILL WIN A TRIP
TO THE U.K. RIGHT AFTER THIS.
>> Announcer: TOMORROW ON
"LIVE," A DANCE PERFORMANCE BY
DEREK HOUGH.
>> Ryan: WELCOME BACK.
THIS IS THE MOMENT WE'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR.
>> Kelly: WE BEEN WAITING FOR
ALL MOMENT, ONE LUCKY PERSON WHO
IS SITTING RIGHT HERE IN OUR
AUDIENCE THIS MORNING IS ABOUT
TO WIN A VACATION AND HE OR SHE
DOESN'T EVEN KNOW IT YET.
>> Ryan: WILL RECEIVE AN
INCREDIBLE TRIP FOR TWO
INCLUDING BUSINESS CLASS AIRFARE
TO EXPLORE SCOTLAND, ENGLAND,
AND WHALES FROM VISIT BRITAIN
VALUED AT $13,000.
>> Kelly: LET'S BRING OUT
PAUL, WHO HAS THE ENVELOPE.
COME ON OUT.
IF PAUL, EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU.
>> Ryan: GREAT JACKET AS WELL.
>> Kelly: RYAN IS REALLY GOOD
AT READING NAMES OFTEN ENVELOPE.
>> Ryan: THE WINNER IS RACHEL
WARREN FROM GARDENA, CALIFORNIA,
WHERE ARE YOU?
WHERE IS RACHEL?
WE SEE YOU RIGHT THERE.
CONGRATULATIONS.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
THE ONE THAT'S EXCITING.
>> Ryan: A SPECIAL THANKS TO
THE ACADEMY OF THE MOTION
PICTURE ARTS AND SCIENCES.
WE WANT AND THANK YOU TO THE
DOLBY THEATRE.
>> Ryan: AND ALSO THANKS TO
OUR FRIENDS FOR DESIGNING THE
BEAUTIFUL GREEN ROOM.
>> Kelly: AND CONGRATULATIONS
AGAIN TO ALL OF THIS YEAR'S
OSCAR WINNERS.
>> Ryan: WE WILL SEE YOU LIVE
IN NEW YORK.
WE HAVE TO GO TO THE AIRPORT
RIGHT NOW.
WHEN WE WILL BE AT THE AIRPORT
IF YOU NEED US.
TO SEE TOMORROW.
>> Ryan: THANK YOU SO MUCH,
HAVE A GREAT DAY.
♪ ♪
Honey you know some things
you can't take back...
...unless you got it from ALDI.
Their Twice as Nice
Guarantee means
if you're not happy
for any reason,
they'll give you a refund
and replace it.
The ALDI Twice as Nice
Guarantee.
ALDI. Shop differentli.
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
Honey you know some things
you can't take back...
...unless you got it from ALDI.
Their Twice as Nice
Guarantee means
if you're not happy
for any reason,
they'll give you a refund
and replace it.
The ALDI Twice as Nice
Guarantee.
ALDI. Shop differentli.
♪ ♪