with Kelly and Ryan."
Today we catch up with
Kate Hudson,
and "Mr. Worldwide,"
Pitbull.
Plus straight from the
big screen, actor Winston Duke,
and a performance
from Daughtry,
all next on "Live."
[Dua Lipa's "Electricity" plays]
And now, here are
Kelly Ripa and Ryan Seacrest.
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: Hello!
>> Kelly: Yep, yep, yep.
>> Now I'm ready.
>> Ryan: Good morning.
[cheers and applause]
Good morning.
[music continues]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
I like that one.
"Electricity," right?
A little Dua Lipa there
in the game.
>> Kelly: Hey, it is Wednesday,
July 3, 2019.
It is my dad's birthday today!
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: Happy birthday,
Joe Ripa.
>> Kelly: Happy birthday,
It's a big one.
I'm not gonna blow up your age.
>> Ryan: Does he have a
traditional celebration?
>> Kelly: Well, you know, every
year, he likes to say that they
do fireworks and they have a big
cookout, but I'm like, "That's
pretty much everybody."
>> Ryan: "You know,
that was for me.
That was for me,
that whole thing up in the sky."
Well, my greatest memory of your
father is he and I laying on a
chaise lounge in the Bahamas
together with him giving me life
advice and guidance and asking
if I wanted representation by
him to negotiate my next deal.
[laughter]
He was gonna be my union member.
>> Kelly: It was the sweet--
he was--
>> Gelman: Joe was trying
to unionize.
>> Kelly: It was--he was--
to unionize us.
He was telling us that we needed
to unionize.
And I said, "We are in a union,
Dad.
We--believe it or not,
we are in a union."
>> Ryan: I felt like he accepted
me in that moment.
>> Kelly: He really did.
The two of you were so--
>> Ryan: Right?
>> Kelly: I have pictures of
that, and they're some of my
favorite memories, because you
two are so funny together,
the two of you.
Because you take on my dad's
personality when you talk
to my dad.
So--you--yeah.
>> Ryan: I became--
I became stern.
>> Kelly: Yeah.
>> Ryan: I became--
my voice got deeper.
>> Kelly: Yeah.
[laughter]
>> Ryan: I find when I talk to,
like, athletes too,
I do the same thing.
>> Kelly: Right.
>> Ryan: Like, I--
So how was the game?
>> Kelly: Yeah.
[laughter]
And you always say to my dad,
"Joe Ripa."
>> Ryan: "Joe Ripa."
>> Kelly: Yeah, it's like you
puff up and then you're like,
"Joe"--
You call him both names...
>> Ryan: "Joe Ripa."
>> Kelly: Which most people do.
Most people call me both names.
>> Ryan: Kelly Ripa.
Yeah, well, it's like one--
I mean, come on.
You--Kelly Ripa.
"There's Kelly Ripa.
There's Kelly Ripa.
Kelly Ripa from the park."
>> Kelly: But I mean, before
this show, I'm going back
to high school.
>> Ryan: Kirripa.
>> Kelly: I was both names.
>> Kelly: Well--
>> Ryan: Kirripa.
>> Kelly: Well, you're--
[laughter]
>> Ryan: I'm--listen. If your--
>> Kelly: You're making me
more of a sound than--
[laughter]
>> Ryan: Well, happy
Fourth of July, Kirripa.
>> Kelly: Thank you.
[chirps]
>> Ryan: I was reading this
about, you know--
thank you for tuning in
in the morning.
I don't know what your morning
routines are,
your morning habits are.
But there's a whole article on
surprising morning habits that
can give you more anxiety.
And just by reading it,
I got more anxiety.
>> Kelly: Right, of course.
Just
you saying the word "anxiety"...
>> Ryan: Gives you--
>> Kelly: Gave me anxiety.
>> Ryan: Cortisol's releasing
right now, isn't it?
>> Kelly: Right now, yeah.
>> Ryan: Is cortisol releasing
into your system?
>> Kelly: Yeah.
>> Ryan: Let it out.
>> Kelly: That's why I stopped
wearing pants with a zipper.
[laughter]
Yeah, can't do it.
>> Ryan: That's the reason.
>> Kelly: That's the reason.
I can't do it.
I can't work in live TV and
have a waistband.
[laughter]
No waist anymore.
I'm like, "Forget it.
The cortisol spikes, it's not
gonna affect me, 'cause my dress
is just gonna widen."
[laughter]
>> Ryan: Do you jump--they say
it's bad for you to jump
right out of bed.
Like, to get right out of bed
is bad.
It causes a spike
in all of that.
>> Kelly: Well...
>> Ryan: Do you jump right out
or do you lay there for--
I lay there and moan
for a minute.
[laughter]
>> Kelly: I usually set Snooze.
I do one snooze.
But--
>> Ryan: I find it to be
painful.
>> Kelly: The snooze?
>> Ryan: Yeah.
'Cause I know it's coming, and
I can't--you know,
it's like that anxiety.
>> Kelly: But I like that.
It's like, I hit Snooze, but
the whole time I'm quasi-awake
knowing that--
>> Ryan: It's coming.
But, see, that gives me anxiety,
knowing it's coming.
>> Kelly: I just burped, and
that gave me anxiety.
>> Ryan: By the way...
[laughter]
Can I say, that garlic
smells great.
>> Kelly: Oh, no, it's not.
It's not garlic.
>> Ryan: No, I know.
You to--I know it's not garlic.
Let's see.
Doing household chores
gives you anxiety, so quit.
>> Kelly: Wait, that gives you
anxiety: Household chores?
>> Gelman: Well, knowing you--
>> Ryan: At the start of your
day--at the start of--this is
all at the beginning of the day.
>> Kelly: Oh, they're saying,
don't do it at the start
of the day.
>> Ryan: Yeah, don't do it at
the beginning of the day.
Don't look at your work email
the second you get out of bed.
Don't look at your to-do list.
Don't skip breakfast.
>> Kelly: [groans]
I mean, I do--I do all of that.
>> Ryan: I know. I know.
>> Kelly: I do every--
>> Ryan: But you get to wear
a dress, and it's all fine.
>> Kelly: Well, I mean, they
make it look fine.
I liken myself to
a Westminster show dog.
[laughter]
Yeah, it looks very fluffy on
the outside, but on the inside,
it's like, "Is this done yet?
Are we over?"
[laughter]
"Can we just--can you please
put me back in my cage?"
[laughter]
"I just--I don't want to--
I don't wa tbere
the judges right now."
[laughter]
>> Ryan: I do find looking at
the phone--I try not to do it
first thing,
which is hard sometimes.
Because you're turning off your
alarm and then--
>> Kelly: I have to look at it,
because usually he's either
texted me or you've texted me
over some thing that's happened
in the middle of the night.
>> Ryan: Some inane thing.
>> Kelly: Yeah, some thing
that has happened.
So I have to check it first
thing in the morning.
Um, you know, it's not just my
dad's birthday today, okay?
I want you to know it's also
another national holiday.
>> Ryan: What is it?
>> Gelman: A special day.
>> Kelly: And I believe it could
become an international holiday
if we get it trending here.
It is national compliment
your mirror day.
>> Gelman: Oh, my goodness.
[cheers and applause]
Yes.
Lady in the front row is like,
"No, it is not."
Like, "Oh, yes, it is."
You want to know how it works?
Watch this.
>> Gelman: Okay.
>> Kelly: Okay, you--
you hold this.
>> Ryan: I'm not complimenting
a picture of me.
>> Kelly: Hold--hold it.
>> Gelman: Just come on.
>> Kelly: Gelman, do you want
to do it too,
and I'll read?
>> Gelman: Sure, I can do it.
Yeah.
>> Kelly: You stand next to
Ryan; I want to see--
>> Ryan: Gelman celebrates this
every day.
>> Kelly: Oh, I know.
Trust me, I know.
>> Gelman: Yeah.
>> Kelly: Here's what you do,
everybody.
Stand in front of your mirror
with your eyes closed.
That's the key.
>> Ryan: That's the key.
>> Kelly: Close your eyes.
>> Ryan: Turn the lights off.
>> Kelly: Yeah.
[clears throat]
Put a big smile on your face.
Eyes closed.
Big smile.
Now, open your eyes.
>> Ryan: No.
[laughter]
I don't want to see it. No.
>> Kelly: Isn't the picture of
the person in the mirror
absolutely stunning?
>> Gelman: Oh, yes.
[laughter]
>> Ryan: Who's making love to
themself over here?
What?
[laughter]
What is going on?
>> Kelly: Don't make the special
holiday be over--overshadowed
by the Fourth of July.
>> Gelman: No.
I'm feeling very positive.
>> Ryan: I have to tell you, I--
>> Kelly: Make sure you
compliment your mirror for
displaying the beautiful
person--
>> Ryan: Oh, gag.
>> Gelman: Thank you, mirror.
[laughter]
What a great mirror you are.
>> Ryan: Gag, gag, gag.
>> Gelman: You're my favorite
mirror.
You're a good mirror.
>> Kelly: Okay, Gelman.
[laughter]
>> Ryan: Goodbye.
>> Kelly: Thank you, Gelman.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: I was reading this
article about smartphones
at the gym.
I guess, you know, a lot of--if
you go to the gym and work out,
the gyms want you to post that
you're working out at the gym
because they get good free
publicity and marketing.
>> Kelly: Well, especially your
gym where all the models go.
[cheers]
>> Kelly: It looks like a
Victoria's Secrets shoot every
time--I'm like, "Oh, there's
Ryan at his gym again."
>> Ryan: Hey, look.
It's the only gym that has
enough weight for me, so--
[laughter]
>> Gelman: Three-pounders?
>> Ryan: Yeah, I have the little
pink ones you hold.
[laughter]
>> Kelly: They sha--
they make sounds.
>> Ryan: Yeah, they make
shaker sounds.
>> Kelly: They make sounds.
>> Ryan: It's got some
Daddy Yankee music.
>> Gelman: Yeah.
>> Ryan: But this article is
about a gym etiquette.
They say don't FaceTime or Skype
in front of other people.
No photos in the locker room.
>> Gelman: No, yeah, no.
>> Ryan: No.
[laughter]
Wait until after a class to ask
the instructor for the selfie.
Now, what I find people do
in the gym is, they take their
phone and they set it up, like,
over here, you know?
And they go over here
to do curls.
And then you walk through their
shot, and--[gasps]
[laughter]
>> Kelly: Yeah, well,
guess what.
Guess what.
That's exactly their problem,
not your problem.
>> Ryan: Yeah, exactly.
>> Kelly: Because that is a--
that's--the floor--this is
gonna sound like a shock
to all the millennials.
The floor is for walking.
[laughter]
>> Ryan: Well, the good--
>> Kelly: It's not an imaginary
tripod for you to lean your cell
phone so you can have a selfie
so you can remember so you can
be nostalgic in real time.
Right?
>> Ryan: Listen.
These are the people that are
celebrating the mirror day all
day today, so they won't be
at the gym.
>> Kelly: That's right.
That's right.
They're taking the day off.
>> Ryan: They're taking
the day off to just celebrate
themselves again.
>> Kelly: Yes, that's true.
>> Ryan: Shall we?
>> Kelly: Um, sure,
we could do that.
I mean, I do have my study out
on insomnia.
>> Gelman: Oh.
>> Ryan: Do it.
>> Kelly: You want to know why
we're so--why we're such
insomniacs?
>> Ryan: Why are we such
>> Kelly: Embarrassing thoughts
keep us awake at night.
[laughter]
>> Ryan: I think just thoughts.
Like--like a sum of all
thoughts keep me awake.
>> Kelly: Well, that's what
I said.
>> Ryan: Everything happens.
>> Kelly: Thoughts keep me
awake at night,
not necessarily embarrassing
thoughts.
>> Ryan: Just the--a flow.
>> Kelly: I am a human
experiment that you cannot die
from embarrassment.
>> Ryan: You are--
that's correct.
>> Kelly: I'm still here.
>> Ryan: You are good on that.
>> Kelly: Right.
So--but they are saying that,
like, daily blunders can creep
into the margins of our brain,
and so we fall asleep but
suddenly the thought of
something mortifying that
happened during the day
creeps in and--
>> Ryan: It does.
>> Kelly: Right.
>> Ryan: It does, but that is
like--there's 40 other thoughts
happening at the same time.
>> Kelly: Right.
>> Ryan: So one by one, shh!
I try and quiet them.
>> Kelly: Right.
>> Ryan: Shh.
Then the alarm goes off.
It's morning; I still--
[laughter]
I'm still trying to quiet them.
>> Kelly: You're trying
to quiet the--
>> Ryan: I'm trying to quiet--
you know, I mean, I try
to quiet the thoughts.
Hard to do sometimes.
>> Kelly: I always worry that
I've hurt somebody's feelings,
and that creeps back to me.
You know, like--you know
my sense of humor.
Sometimes I'll, like--
>> Ryan: Yeah.
>> Kelly: I'll use some of my
best stuff on people
I don't know that well,
and they're like--
>> Ryan: Right, and they take--
>> Kelly: And I go, "No,
I'm kidding.
See, that's my"--
>> Ryan: "That's my
personality."
[laughter]
>> Kelly: And then that creeps
in at night.
I go, "Oh, I don't think
so-and-so got my humor
at the funeral today."
[laughter]
Right?
>> Ryan: No, I've never
had that happen.
Today on the show?
>> Gelman: Yeah, we--
>> Ryan: Kate Hudson is here.
Ready for Kate Hudson?
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: Pitbull is also here.
>> Ryan: Winston Duke is here.
>> Kelly: Yeah, and a
performance by Daughtry.
>> Ryan: Now, tomorrow's the
Fourth of July, and all week
long, we're playing a special
audience edition of Stump the
Hosts where an audience member
shares a summer-themed truth
or lie and we have to figure out
which one is true.
>> Kelly: Yeah, if they stump
us, they get a "Kelly and Ryan"
mug and a $1,200 appliance
package from Cuisinart.
That's right.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: All right?
>> Kelly: So far this week,
we have not--that's right--
not been stumped.
But the week is...
>> Gelman: It's still young.
>> Ryan: The week is young.
>> Kelly: Still young.
>> Ryan: Cover your mug, Kelly.
>> Kelly: All right.
>> Ryan: It's time for Stump
the Hosts: Audience Edition.
[cheers and applause]
>> ♪ Pump up the jam ♪
♪ Pump it up ♪
♪ While your feet are stompin' ♪
♪ And the jam is pumpin' ♪
♪ Look at here ♪
♪ The crowd is jumpin' ♪
♪ Pump it up a little more ♪
♪ Get the party going ♪
♪ On the dance floor ♪
♪ See, 'cause that's where ♪
♪ The party's at ♪
♪ And you'll find out ♪
♪ If you do that ♪
>> Ryan: See them all
on the dance floor.
♪ ♪
There she is.
[cheers and applause]
You know her, you love her as
Jessica Jackson from Phoenix,
Arizona.
Jessica, happy Fourth.
>> Kelly: Hi.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: Good to have you
with us.
>> Kelly: That's the other
Jessie J.
>> Ryan: [laughs]
So we're gonna meet the studio
audience member now, right?
>> Kelly: Yeah, that's right.
Let's meet our participant from
Knoxville, Tennessee.
Where is Kristy Bruce?
[cheers and applause]
Hi.
>> Ryan: Hi, Kristy.
>> Kelly: Hi, adorable.
>> Hey, girl.
>> Kelly: How you doing?
>> Hi.
>> Ryan: Hi!
>> Kelly: Hi!
>> Ryan: How you doing?
>> I'm great.
How are you doing?
>> Ryan: It's a pleasure.
>> Kelly: I gotta tell you,
Kristy Bruce, you have an
absolute joyful, joyful
sunshine face.
>> Oh, thank you.
>> Kelly: You really do.
[cheers and applause]
You have a smile
that makes me smile.
>> Oh, well, good. I'm glad.
>> Kelly: Yeah, that's good.
So you should win bonus points.
>> Ryan: We hope so.
>> Yes, yes. Bonus points, yes.
>> Kelly: Just for that.
>> Ryan: So you're gonna give us
two statements.
>> Okay.
>> Ryan: All right?
We're gonna try and guess
which is true.
If you stump us, you win.
Okay.
All right, this is gonna
be hard.
>> Both: Okay.
>> All right, here we go.
The first lie--
or no, the first truth or lie
is, um...
Growing up, we had a houseboat,
on Norris Lake in Knoxville,
Tennessee, and my family had
a boat, and we would all ski.
We would all do it--
there were four of us,
sometimes five.
We would all line up and we
would do pyramids.
>> Kelly: Behind the houseboat.
>> Behind the house--
well, not the houseboat, 'cause
we had a boat, but we kind of
just--
>> Ryan: So you had a houseboat
and a ski boat.
>> Right.
So we would--we would go out
and we would ski out and
sometimes we would compete.
We were the McMichaels.
We would travel and do
local competitions.
>> Ryan: All right,
what's the second one?
Then we'll start
asking questions.
>> The second one is, I was
Miss Tiny Tot of Tennessee.
>> Kelly: [gasps]
>> And on Fourth of July,
I would do the Fourth of July
parade and sit on the
convertible and wave
to the crowd.
Yeah.
>> Kelly: Okay, let me see
your parade wave.
>> Well, it was bad,
because my mom told me--
you know, I would wave like
this, you know, to everybody.
They were like, "No, no, no.
You've got to--
you gotta give it.
You know, you gotta
give it good."
>> Kelly: And how old were you
when you were Miss Tiny Tot?
>> I was seven.
>> Kelly: Seven.
>> Ryan: Is Miss Tiny Tot...
>> Kelly: I don't care.
I wantnt her to be Miss Tiny To,
because--
[laughter]
I'm like, you're Miss Tiny Tot
of this show.
>> Ryan: Is there a Miss
Tiny Tot circuit out there?
>> Miss Tiny Tot.
>> Kelly: It's very rare that I
am bigger than somebody.
>> Both: Yes.
>> Ryan: What does the audience
think?
What does the audience have to
say about this?
Oh, wow.
>> Kelly: Oh, wow.
>> Ryan: I mean, they really
believe you have all those
boats.
>> Kelly: But I want her to be
Miss--
Oh!
What is going on right now?
>> Ryan: It's staying 80/20.
>> Kelly: I wanna believe that--
>> Ryan: Do you want to go
with it, Kel?
>> Gelman: Go with what you--
>> Ryan: You know, it's your
father's birthday.
>> Gelman: All right.
>> Ryan: You go with
what you want.
>> Uh-uh.
>> Kelly: She--
[laughter]
>> I'm not gonna say a word.
>> Kelly: Um...
All right, let's just say that
I'll go with the audience and
say that she was part of a
waterskiing troop.
>> Ryan: Is that true?
>> No.
I was Miss Tiny Tot
of Tennessee.
[cheers and applause]
You wanted me to be Miss
Tiny Tot, and I was!
[cheers and applause]
I was Miss Leprechaun too.
>> Kelly: I--you were?
>> Oh, yeah, I had multiple
titles.
>> Ryan: You are amazing.
>> Kelly: She's a multiple
title winner!
>> Gelman: Jeez.
>> Ryan: She's going down in
history, ladies and gentlemen.
>> Kelly: All right, so now you
help a member of our studio
audience receive a $500 gift
card from Club Monaco.
>> Ryan: All right,
so get out your tickets.
>> Can I pick one of my friends?
>> Kelly: Yeah, you pick--
Uh, you can--if you can find
their number, you can pick one
of your friends.
>> Okay.
>> Gelman: No looking.
>> I'm looking.
I'm looking, Christy Vining.
I'm looking.
I'm just kidding.
Uh, let's see here.
125.
>> Ryan: 125.
>> 125?
There you go.
>> Kelly: All right.
>> Ryan: Right over there in
the corner.
>> That was so fun.
>> Ryan: Kristy, so nice to meet
you.
>> You too.
You're a blast.
>> Ryan: We'll be right back
with Kate Hudson.
[cheers and applause]
>> Announcer: Still ahead on
"Live," a performance
by Daughtry,
actor Winston Duke, Pitbull,
and coming up next, Kate Hudson.
>> Kelly: She's a successful
actress, a bestselling author,
a clothing entrepreneur,
and one of the most lovable
people we know.
Please welcome back to the show
Kate Hudson.
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
>> Ryan: Good to see you.
>> Good to see you.
Thanks!
>> Kelly: It's so funny.
I saw that dress hanging
backstage, and I was like--
>> Yes!
>> Kelly: I was like,
"Oh, my gosh."
>> I made it.
>> Kelly: I thought that was
for me.
[laughter]
>> Ryan: She can get you one.
>> I'll get you one.
>> Kelly: It is very cute.
>> It's made out of
organic cotton.
>> Kelly: No kidding.
>> Yeah.
>> Kelly: So pretty.
>> Ah, I'm excited
to talk about it.
But first I want to say that I--
I would--you took my job.
I would love to be in a bikini
pointing at cars.
>> Ryan: Oh, really?
>> Kelly: Well, you could be.
>> I love a fast car.
>> Kelly: Listen.
>> And I love a bikini.
>> Ryan: Do you--hey.
Do you remember the Whitesnake
video where they were
dancing on the--
>> Yes.
>> Kelly: Yeah, of course.
>> Ryan: That could be us
on the hood.
>> Totally into it.
>> Kelly: Let's--okay.
I smell a tape piece.
>> Ryan: Hey, Gelman.
[laughter]
We're just booking the show
left and right.
So you are a mom of...
>> Kelly: Three.
>> Ryan: Three now.
>> Three, yeah.
Or five--
[cheers and applause]
I say 500.
It's like it feels like I have
500 kids.
That's what it feels like.
>> Kelly: You go from man-to-man
defense to zone defense.
>> Whoo!
>> Kelly: And I don't know what
that means; it just seems like
it ratchets up a lot.
>> Oh, my god.
And everyone's like,
"How are you?"
And I'm like, "Exhausted."
I'm so tired.
>> Ryan: How old is the--six
months is the latest addition?
>> She's six months yesterday.
>> Kelly: Oh, is she cute.
>> Ryan: Oh, my god.
>> Look at her little thighs.
>> Ryan: That's--
>> Oh, my god, you guys.
>> Kelly: Do you ever--
do you chew on her legs?
>> I'm out of my mind.
>> Kelly: You chew on her.
>> I chew on everything.
>> Kelly: Mm-hmm.
>> I'm--I mean, we're all
out of our minds with Rani.
She is so cute.
>> Ryan: I love your
copper pans, though.
Those are nice in the kitchen.
>> Oh, yeah?
>> Ryan: Yeah.
>> Kelly: Copper pans?
You noticed pans?
>> I have copper pans.
>> Ryan: Yeah, she has beautiful
copper pans.
>> I actually collect
>> Ryan: Oh, you do?
>> Yeah.
>> Ryan: Oh, well, see?
>> And I engrave them
and everything.
>> Ryan: Look at that.
>> Yeah.
>> Kelly: It's so funny.
I was so busy looking at the
babe, I did--I was like,
"Copper pans?"
>> Ryan's like,
"Nice copper pans."
>> Ryan: Yeah, I'm--I'm
installing a kitchen right now.
>> Kelly: Is she--are her big
brothers involved or are they
like, at the place where
they're like, "Oh, that's"--you
know, like, "That's a diaper"?
>> Ryder's 15, which is crazy.
I mean, it's like, I mean,azy.
he's almost--he's getting
up to 6 feet.
And he's such a great boy.
>> Ryan: He's a man.
>> Young man.
>> Ryan: Yeah.
>> [mimics sobbing]
>> Kelly: It's okay.
>> But the other day, we were--
I know.
I'm like, what is it?
He's so old.
Uh, but no, he--the other day,
we went to breakfast, and I was
juggling a million things, and
I think it's like, you know,
really wise to go alone
with three kids.
You know, it's like, "Hey,
let's go to breakfast, kids."
And then next thing you know,
I'm not eating, I'm juggling
everything, and I go to Ryder,
"Ryder, just take Rani," and I
went to go get my food at the
buffet, and I looked over, and
here's this young man holding
his sis--I--it was the
craziest image to me.
and I just thought, life is
really weird.
>> Ryan: And it goes fast.
>> It's so fast--
yeah, but I was like, 12
when I--I mean, I--
>> Ryan: You were 12
when you had him?
>> Yeah, in terms of, like,
a Hollywood actress.
>> Kelly: Right.
>> I say in terms of a
Hollywood actress, I was like a
teen mom.
I mean, that's--you know.
Yeah, me and Reese
were like teen moms.
>> Kelly: Yeah, that's true.
>> Like, we had kids really
super young.
>> Ryan: I mean, just from your
posts, like, you don't let
being a busy mom not have
you have fun.
Like, you still, like, really--
[laughter]
Yeah, you know what I mean?
Like, you still are you.
>> Kelly: But don't you think
you learned that
from your family?
Like, your family--when I look
at your family, it's with,
like, admiration and envy,
'cause you all seem like
you're having fun...
>> Both: All the time.
>> Yeah, my parents left us to
have fun all the time.
Yeah, it was like,
"Where are you going?"
They're like, "We're going
to Tahiti."
[laughter]
Okay.
>> Ryan: See you in two weeks!
>> Yeah, exactly.
Uh, no.
Yeah, I--we do.
We--we have fun.
I mean, I--I make sure that,
you know, kids are good and that
I take time to, you know...
>> Ryan: To enjoy.
>> Let out some steam.
Although, lately it's been hard,
'cause I'm still breastfeeding.
I gotta be honest.
>> Kelly: Yeah.
>> It's like my 40th is coming
up, and I keep saying, I'm
just--I deserve a really good
hangover, and it's gonna happen.
>> Kelly: Listen.
I want to give you
a birthday present.
I will watch your children so
you can go tie one on.
I will do the whole--
>> Ryan: And I'll--and I'll go
tie one on with you.
>> That's good. Perfect.
>> Kelly: I will take care--
I will take care of the babies.
I'm very responsible.
So now there's--
>> Ryan: Break it down.
>> Kelly: Musicians in your
family.
You're very musical.
>> I love to sing.
>> Kelly: Yeah.
>> And I play piano.
>> Kelly: I didn't know that.
>> Yeah, but it's like--I keep
forgetting I can't swear on
these shows.
I almost went there.
I'm not very good at it.
I'm--I can write on the piano,
but I can't, like, sit down and
read music and be like,
you know--
>> Kelly: Play a concerto.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Ryan: Well, why don't you
release a single?
>> I have a movie coming out--
I think it's gonna be in the
fall--that's a musical
that Sia directed.
>> Kelly: Oh.
>> Ryan: Oh, wow.
>> Yeah, it's the first time
I've actually sang contemporary
music.
That's really exciting.
And I think after that, I'll
probably--even just because
I feel--I feel like it's one of
those things I have to do at
some point
is, I just have to put something
out there.
>> Ryan: Listen.
>> I don't care what it does.
>> Ryan: Do a--
>> Kelly: You know people that
work on the radio.
>> Oh, yeah, that's right.
>> Ryan: Yeah.
>> [laughs] Oh, that guy.
>> Ryan: I tell you how to
make it a hit.
>> Yeah.
>> Ryan: Collaborate with
DJ Khaled.
>> Right.
>> Ryan: That's all you
gotta do.
Just get DJ Khaled, Kate Hudson.
>> Kelly: Or Mr. Worldwide.
>> Ryan: Or Mr. Worldwide.
>> Or Mr. Worldwide.
>> Ryan: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> Kelly: Mm-hmm.
>> I got it.
I miss--you know what, though.
I have to say, I miss bands.h.
I really do.
Like, my son's really musical.
Bing is insane--like, almost--
he has drums.
I can't get him out of his
drumming room.
>> Ryan: That's great.
>> He's now started playing
keyboard, and he's never
had a piano.
Oh, yeah, he's not even
eight years old.
>> Ryan: He's got it
in the genes.
>> It's kind of crazy.
And I just thought, you know,
"Oh, he's gonna get in a band
and, like, ugh,
it's gonna be tough."
>> Ryan: Yeah, yeah, he's gonna
tour the world.
>> It's gonna be a hard life.
>> Kelly: Yeah, but it's an
exciting life, don't you think?
>> Being a--a touring musician?
>> Ryan: Well, she was--you
have some experience with that.
>> I mean, it's--it's a lot of
work, you know?
And it's amazing when you love
it, but it's a whole different--
like, jazz cats, like all the
people that are, like, I'm
really close to and touring
musicians who still, like,
spend, you know,
200 days a year...
>> Both: On the road.
It's a lot.
>> Kelly: I'm thinking about
your parents, right?
They were probably like,
"Oh, gosh, not acting.
It's such a--like, an unstable
career," right?
If you have a calling for it...
>> Yeah, do it.
>> Kelly: Imagine if your mom
said to you, "Kate, listen.
Anything but acting."
>> Yeah, I would have been
very--
yeah, it would have been hard.
>> Ryan: But you're
entrepreneuring.
I mean, you've got all of these
fashion brands.
You've got a new fashion.
>> I just can't stop working.
>> Ryan: Great.
>> I love to work and, like, I--
>> Kelly: Well,
you're good at it.
>> I've always wanted to design
clothes, and--
>> Ryan: What's Happy x Nature?
>> So Happy x Nature is my
first, like, ready to wear
fashion line.
>> Kelly: It's fantastic.
I'm so happy for you.
>> Thank you.
I'm really excited.
I'm excited.
It's one of those things.
I've been working
really hard on it.
I feel like every time I put my
name to anything, whether I'm
endorsing it or making it like
this, I have to believe in it
and it has to be something that
I feel is important.
And so this is a very
eco-friendly line, and the
fashion industry is like the
worst--number two worst carbon
footprint of all industries.
And I really feel like the
fashion industry needs to look
at how they're making things and
start changing the way that they
do stuff, and it's--
I feel like we--
[cheers and applause]
Yeah.
>> Kelly: Well--
>> And I feel like we're gonna
really hopefully make an impact
there.
>> Kelly: Well,
you're a nature girl.
You grew up in nature,
really, I mean, so--
>> Yeah.
>> Ryan: In Brentwood.
>> In Brent--
>> Kelly: No, but she also--
Colo--she's a Colorado girl.
>> Ryan: Oh, Colorado.
Okay.
>> And then Brentwood.
>> Ryan: Then Brentwood.
[laughter]
>> Kelly: Um, and this,
this is--
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Ryan: Um, all right.
>> Kelly: This is beautiful.
>> Thank you.
>> Ryan: So you can go to our
website for more information
about Kate's fashion line,
Happy x Nature.shion line,
[cheers and applause]
Great to see you.
>> Announcer: Still ahead on
"Live," we'll talk with Pitbull.
>> ♪ Excuse me, excuse me ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
>> Kelly: Mr. Worldwide dancers.
>> Ryan: Yeah, you and me both.
>> Kelly: Right?
>> Ryan: He is a Grammy-winning
international superstar,
Mr. 305, Mr. Worldwide.
Please welcome Pitbull.
[cheers and applause]
>> Whoo! Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo!
[upbeat music]
Got 'em.
Got 'em, got 'em, got 'em.
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: Hi!
>> How you doing?
>> Kelly: How are you?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Ryan: Good to see you, baby.
>> Ryan: Love it.
I mean, the fans--
the fans go nuts.
>> Kelly: [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> Ryan: Armando fans are here.
>> Whoo-hoo!
[cheers and applause]
I think--I think I got the
wrong glasses on.
>> Kelly: Oh, yeah, yeah.
[laughter]
Oh, my gosh.
I know.
I'm sorry.
You look--
>> Ryan: Studious.
>> But I can see everybody
really close right now.
[laughter]
>> Kelly: Sorry about that.
Sorry.
>> Ryan: So listen.
You just...
>> Boom. There we go.
>> Ryan: To go back, for people
who don't know your story.
It is an incredible story.
>> Been very blessed.
Thank God.
And thanks to the fans.
I wouldn't be here
without y'all.
>> Ryan: I'm gonna talk about--
[cheers and applause]
The challenges at the beginning
for you
and what you did to overcome,
to get to be who you are now.
>> Well, I mean, uh, oof.
A lot of different obstacles,
but I think that that's what
makes the journey fun.s what
You know, from nothing
to something.
A whole lot of "no"s,
that's for sure.
And a whole lot of "you can't,"
"you won't," "you never will,"
"don't," "you're crazy,"
"how dare you?"
"Impossible."
And then I flipped every word,
by the way.
So my daughter taught me in the
word "impossible" is "possible."
>> Both: Yeah.
>> Right?
And I took the word "can't"
is "can."
"Won't" is "won."
"Don't" is "do."
And that's exactly what we doing
with our career.
>> Kelly: It's really--
>> 20 years in the game, baby.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: 20 years too, yeah.
>> Kelly: Isn't that great?
>> Ryan: That's amazing.
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: You got your first
record deal from a rap battle.
>> Yeah, it was a rap battle
against--back in the day,
it was a crew called
the Ruff Ryders.
A guy named DMX
was a part of it.
I was very--I was invited to
his video shoot, and I battled
this guy named Drag-On
at the video shoot.
Swizz Beatz was there.
And Swizz Beatz told me, "I'll
give you three rounds with the
drag"--he's a dragon, you know?
"He's gonna burn you."
I was like, "Man, I'm just happy
to be here."
>> Kelly: Right.
[laughter]
>> I had home court advantage.
It was in Miami.
>> Both: Yeah.
>> Okay.
I flipped a coupuple words in
Spanish here and there, called
out a couple neighborhoods that
worked out, you know?
And we won.
>> Kelly: Oh, my god.
That's great.
And that's where it all started.
>> Yep.
You know what's crazy is, is
that's on video.
And the footage, you can't find
it anywhere.
>> Ryan: Really?
>> Crazy enough, yeah.
There's a guy out there.
Jamie, if you're looking at
this, I know you still got
that footage.
>> Kelly: Jamie.
>> Ryan: Let's go. Cough it up.
>> We need to show the world
that, Jamie.
>> Kelly: I would love
to see that.
>> Oh, you will. You will.
Now that I said that,
you'll see it.
It'll be out--
>> Ryan: And also when you were
growing up and your mom would
put on tapes of Tony Robbins
in the car, right?
>> So I lived in a neighborhood
called Carol City in Miami.
And I was not trying to listen
to Tony Robbins.
And whenever my mom could take
me to school, it was a '82 Pinto
that she would take me
to school in.
And she said--she put Tony on.
I wanted to hear, like,
2 Live Crew and Poison Clan.
[laughter]
So one day I go to change the
radio, you know, to my music,
and she's like, "Bam."
And she said, "Do you pay
for this car?"
I said, "No."
She said, "Well, then
don't touch my radio."
[laughter]
>> Kelly: And so you were
listening to Tony Robbins?
>> So subliminally, I started
listening to Tony, and all it
took was one story, which is the
story about Colonel Sanders and
how it took him 1,007 "no"s
before he could sell his recipe.
And I thought about it, like,
"Man, it's hard to get one 'no'
out of my mom."
Like, man,
imagine 1,007 of 'em.
So the word "no" became "yes."
You know?
I welcome failure.
I welcome the slip.
I welcome the fall.
I welcome the "no."
I mean, well, you guys know.
>> Kelly: Yeah, of course.
>> Yeah, and failure's the
mother of all success, and I've
learned that throughout the
game, and every record that has
been huge for us around the
world thanks to you guys,
every record exec said,
"Not gonna work."
So the minute that they do say,
"Oh, that's a hit,"
I'm like, "Oh, throw that out
the window."
[laughter]
>> Ryan: It's--it's true.
It's true.
I mean, you've had--it's like--
I have the fortunate opportunity
to play Pitbull's music
every single day.
>> Well, I put you in one of
the records.
>> Ryan: He put me in a lyric.
I was so excited.
>> And I--
>> Kelly: Wait, wait, wait.
What lyric?
>> It was, um...
"Give Me Everything."
>> Ryan: Which is a huge
global hit.
>> Where I said,
"My family's from Cuba,
but I'm an American idol,
getting money
like Seacrest."
>> Kelly: Oh, yes!
[laughter]
>> Ryan: More with Pitbull;
how he became an ugly dog
after this.
>> Yee-ow!
>> Announcer: Tomorrow on
"Live," the cast of
"Stranger Things."
>> You call that a dog?
[dog growls]
It's all right, guys.
Slick Dog's got this.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
>> What are you doing?
>> Having fun,
getting crazy,
getting loose.
Go. I'll stall him.
Go! Go, go!
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: That's great.
>> Kelly: Something
for the parents.
Little something
>> Yeah.
>> Kelly: That's a scene from
"UglyDolls" starring Pitbull.
>> Yeah.
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: You play a character
named Uglydog.
>> Yeah, you know, I--you know,
the people at the studio really
thought this out thoroughly, and
they was like, "You know,
your name's Pitbull.
We want you to play this dog."
[laughter]
I was like, "Man, you guys are
geniuses."
>> Ryan: With a--with
an alter ego, though.
>> Yeah, but it's great.
Well, you know, that's why I
brought the glasses out today,
'cause I'm also Slick Dog.
>> Both: Right.
>> So I'm Uglydog and Slick Dog
in the movie.
And what I love about this
movie, really--you know, why I
signed up for it, it's thehy I
perfect time for the perfect
message to let everybody know
that believe it or not,
perfection doesn't exist.
>> Ryan: Yeah.
>> You know?
[cheers and applause]
And also flip the word "ugly,"
which the word "ugly" is
"You gotta love yourself."
Okay?
[cheers and applause]
And--
[laughter]
Learning a little bit today,
huh?
>> Ryan: Yeah.
>> And especially in a society
where you got all the kids right
now on social media, and it's
all about followers and likes
when it really should be about
leaders and unique.
That's what it--you know, who
cares--forget about following.
You know, be yourself.
Love yourself.
And that's what this movie
is all about.
You got Uglyville and
Perfectville.
And guess what?
Everybody in Uglyville, man,
they love each other, they have
fun with each other, make fun of
each other, they enjoy
each other.
Everybody in Perfectville, they
just, you know, everybody does
the same thing and they all look
the same and they all--
so Uglyville--I can't spoil
the movie for y'all.
[laughter]
You know?
>> Ryan: They're getting loose
in Uglyville.
>> I get loose, I have fun, you
know, I get a chance to enjoy
and so it was a lot of fun.
Obviously you see I'm very
excited about it.
And they gave me a chance to
actually be me in a cartoon
character.
>> Kelly: It's really great.
>> Yeah, it's fun.
A lot of fun.
>> Ryan: Have you thought about
being you in a movie?
>> Well, you know, let me tell
you, I'm Mr. Worldwide.
All right?
But Ryan, okay--
Ryan is Mr. Nonexclusive.
[laughter]
This man has a deal
with everybody.
[laughter]
So I'm like, "Ryan, how can
I use your attorney, okay?"
[laughter]
So you would understand me when
it comes to movies.
I'm more--I like to be more
off-camera, invest and be
partners in it.
>> Kelly: So are you saying you
want Ryan to star as you--
>> Oh, that would be great.
That would be great.
[cheers and applause]
There you go.
What?
Yeah!
Get it, get it, get it.
[laughter]
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: I just would watch it
all day.
Don't hate.
>> Oh, that was great.
>> Kelly: That's the greatest
thing I've ever seen.
[cheers and applause]
"UglyDolls," make sure
you check it out.
[cheers and applause]
>> Announcer: Friday on "Live,"
Ricky Gervais.
>> Ryan: He is an award-winning
actor.
We know him as M'Baku
from "Black Panther."
And now he stars in Jordan
Peele's new thriller "Us."
Please welcome Winston Duke,
everybody.
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
>> Kelly: How are you?
>> So great. So great.
>> Kelly: So happy to see you.
>> Ryan: How are you?
>> Good to see you, man.
>> Ryan: Good to see you.
>> Oh, wonderful.
>> Ryan: Oh, he feels like
an Oscar winner.
>> Kelly: Oh, he does.
Yes, you actually
look like an Oscar winner.
>> From your lips to God's ears.
>> Kelly: Yes, yes.
>> Ryan: Well, you guys did--
you won some Oscars
for "Black Panther."
>> Yeah, we got three Oscars for
"Black Panther."
>> Kelly: What a thrill.
>> Yes.
>> Kelly: I mean, really,
what a thrill.
And is the sequel--are you
working on the sequel?
Can we talk about that yet?
>> Is that your, like, smooth
pitch to find out
what's going on?
>> Kelly: No, just trying to
figure out if there was a sequel
in the works.
>> Yeah, there's definitely
a "Black Panther 2"...
>> Kelly: Good.
>> In the works.
[cheers and applause]
Everything's very hush-hush
with Marvel and Disney around
it, but you know, if you're
eager for M'Baku fix, I'll be
in the "Avengers: Infinity War"
part 2.
>> Kelly: Okay, great.
>> So that's coming.
>> Ryan: So that's coming
as well.
And we understand you're
celebrating all the success.
You bought a house?
>> I did.
I did.
>> Ryan: Congratulations,
Happy homeowner.
>> Thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: That's what it is.
I thought--I thought you looked
more burdened than the last time
I saw you.
>> I think it's with all
the home renovations,
that's what it is.
You know, finding furniture
that fits.
>> Kelly: Exactly.
>> Yes, yes.
Especially 'cause I'm a big guy,
so I'm always trying to make the
things work, but you know, it's
all about size and scale.
>> Kelly: You want
a sumptuous sofa.
>> I like that word.
>> Kelly: Yes.
>> Yeah, sumptuous.
>> Kelly: Yeah.
>> Ryan: So you have to--
you actually are shopping for
larger than normal--
>> Um, not nor--
larger than normal.
It's just things that fit me
but also are in proportion
to the home.
>> Kelly: You know, these chairs
seem to fit you well.
Maybe you'd like to--
>> These work great.
I might take these.
>> Kelly: These could be great
for the--for the dining room?
>> Is this a gift?
>> Kelly: Yes, absolutely.
This is a gift.
Gelman, we need new chairs.
[laughter]
>> Ryan: Are you moving anything
from your current place
into the new place?
>> Um, a couple things.
But really, it's mainly our
first family home
in the States, you know?
>> Kelly: So great.
>> So it's been just a pleasure
to be able to do that, be the
first one to purchase--
>> Ryan: Oh, but you have--
he has citrus.
>> I do.
>> Ryan: She wants--that's her
dream is to have citrus.
>> Kelly: My dream is to have a
citrus plant of some kind.
I live in New York City, so that
dream is probably never
going to happen.
Ryan, unbeknownst to me,
in all the years--
>> Ryan: I was keeping it on the
DL like the sequel.
>> Kelly: Has an orange grove.
>> Oh, my god.
>> Kelly: He has a secret
orange grove.
What do you have?
>> Ryan: In my secret garden.
>> I have kumquats.
>> Kelly: Oh, no kidding.
>> Kumquats.
And I actually--
>> Kelly: The baby orange.
>> [laughs]
>> Ryan: You can eat them whole.
You can eat them whole.
>> Yes, actually 'cause the skin
is sweet and the inside is sour.
>> Kelly: Yes.
>> So there this, like,
awesome little fruit.
>> Kelly: You can make a chutney
out of it.
>> Ooh!
>> Kelly: I will make you
some kumquat chutney.
>> Ooh, she said "chutney."
>> Kelly: I will make you
a chutney.
>> Can you say it again?
>> Kelly: Chutney.
You could make a chutney
out of your kumquats.
Did you know that?
>> Yes, yes.
And I have a little present
for you.
I brought you some of
my kumquats.
>> Kelly: No, you did not.
>> I did.
>> Kelly: Are these your
kumquats?
>> These are my kumquats.
>> Kelly: I am going to
chutney this.
[cheers and applause]
Oh, my god.
Really?
You just pop one right in?
>> Yeah.
>> Ryan: They're like satisfying
in a poppy way.
>> Yeah, yeah.
They're intense.
They're very intense.
>> Ryan: You can eat
the whole thing.
>> Kelly: Mmm.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> Ryan: Do you have a--
>> Kelly: These are fresh.
>> Yeah, they're very fresh.
[laughter]
They're from my tree.
Winston's own.
[laughter]
>> Kelly: We're gonna make you--
we're gonna make--we're gonna
manufacture your chutney.
>> Let's do it.
>> Kelly: M'Baku's chutney.
[laughter]
>> M'Baku's vegetarian chutney.
>> Kelly: Tell me that--
>> I think that's a glorious--
>> Kelly: That is a
trillion-dollar idea.
>> Ryan: Do you cook?
I'm gonna grab my--
>> I cook a little bit.
But because my size is always
going up and down
for each role--
>> Ryan: Yeah, I know
the feeling.
[laughter]
>> Kelly: Do you have to do that
a lot?
>> A lot. A lot.
So for M'Baku, I gained
about 40 pounds.
And then for upcoming movie,
"Us," Jordan Peele didn't want
me to feel like a superhero, so
he was like, "If you could just
eat some burgers or something."
So you can look just like a dad
who has responsibilities
other than going to the gym.
>> Kelly: Isn't that amazing?
Like, it's--and I think that
this is a uniquely male thing
that men in their roles can go
up and down the scale with
relative ease.
Like, just have a couple of
burgers.
>> Yeah.
It's--it's--it's--that was
fun, but then losing the weight
is not.
>> Kelly: No, oh, okay.
Well, I'm glad to hear you
say that.
>> Ryan: Let's take
a break and--
this is your tree.
Just plant those and you'll have
your very own citrus tree.
>> Kelly: Until the first frost.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: We'll come right back
and talk about "Us"
right after this.
>> ♪ In the house ♪
♪ Where the heart don't cry ♪
>> Announcer: Tomorrow on
"Live," a performance by O.A.R.
>> ♪ And I'm ♪
♪ Dreaming of you tonight ♪
>> Now, I thought I already done
told y'all to get off
my property.
Okay?
So if y'all want to get crazy,
we can get crazy!
Now, the cops are already
on they way.
>> [clicking]
>> Hey.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: [laughing]
>> You got goosebumps?
>> Kelly: Yes.
>> Ryan: We are scared
in thrillers like this.
>> Kelly: Yes.
Jordan Peele, I am convinced,
is a terrifying person
in real life.
>> [laughter]
He actually is really just like
a calm, smooth, unassuming guy.
And you'd never think that was
going on up there.
>> Kelly: What is going on
up there, though?
>> Yeah, that's really
the thing.
>> Kelly: How does he come up
with these scenarios?
>> I think he's just very
imaginative, and you know, his
take on American cinema--
'cause I feel that's really what
"Get Out" and this movie is
doing is interrogating America
as a culture
with really interesting
"what-if"s.
>> Ryan: How many people
live through this?
'Cause it looks--
>> I can't tell you that one.
>> Ryan: Do you survive?
>> Ryan: What can you tell us
about this?
>> Kelly: What can you tell us
about "Us"?
[laughter]
What can you tell us?
>> What I can say is that it's
deeply really just a family
drama.
It's about a family caught in an
interesting scenario, and they
have to fight for their lives,
and they're confronted with
essentially their own demons,
which are these doppelganger
figures.
>> Ryan: Oh, boy.
>> That look exactly like them.
>> Ryan: But at least
you have a bat.
>> Yeah.
>> Kelly: I mean, look--I just
want to--I want everybody to
look at that photo.
>> Hmm.
>> Kelly: Tell--that is--
I mean--
>> Ryan: Terrifying.
>> Yeah.
>> Kelly: Terrifying.
>> It's terrifying and then,
you know, being in that space,
being in that headspace and that
body was really tough to stay
in, because you had to go a--
I have to go to a really
interesting place.
But we're--we were
well supported.
>> Kelly: Was it a heavy place?
>> Um, heavy emotionally,
because--I can't tell you
anything without giving
a big spoiler.
But it's a dark place for these
characters, and I never
judge them.
I never looked at them
as any kind of a villain.
>> Kelly: You can't, can you?
>> At all.
So that was a really big
important part of doing the work
is not judging those characters,
especially these ones.
And you'll find out
really soon why.
>> Ryan: Well, we truly get to
see your versatility in
everything that you do.
Great to have you with us, man.
>> Kelly: I love--
I love a Jordan Peele film.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: Winston Duke.
>> Announcer: If you'd like to
know more about anything you see
on "Live," just log on toyou see
our website at kellyandryan.com.
>> Announcer: Closed captioning
sponsored in part by...
>> Ryan: Make sure and join us
tomorrow for an all-new
Fourth of July party
with special house band, O.A.R.
>> Kelly: That's very exciting.
>> Ryan: So we'll be here
for that.
Now singing "Backbone" from
their album "Cage to Rattle,"
it is Daughtry.
Let's go.
[cheers and applause]
[music]
♪ ♪
>> Hey!
Hey!
♪ ♪
♪ When you're hurting ♪
♪ Deep down ♪
♪ When you're feelin' ♪
♪ Like you're never gonna ♪
♪ Dig your way out ♪
♪ Never gonna dig your way out ♪
♪ Keep pushing up the river ♪
♪ Keep mining for the silver ♪
♪ Till you've shot gold ♪
♪ Gotta weather the storm ♪
♪ 'Cause it can't rain forever ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ I'm telling you ♪
♪ We all fall on hard times ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ Each day is a hard climb ♪
♪ Some days, your body ♪
♪ Has to carry on ♪
♪ So you gotta show ♪
♪ A little backbone ♪
>> ♪ Ooh-ooh-whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
>> ♪ You know ♪
>> ♪ Ooh-ooh-whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
>> ♪ You know ♪
>> ♪ Ooh-ooh-whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
>> ♪ You know ♪
>> ♪ Ooh-ooh-whoo-ooh ♪
>> ♪ You gotta show ♪
♪ A little backbone ♪
♪ These troubles, so real ♪
♪ We're all facing
♪ Temptations ♪
♪ And our own fears ♪
♪ Year after year ♪
♪ 'Cause it can't rain forever ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ I'm telling you ♪
♪ We all fall on hard times ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ Each day is a hard climb ♪
♪ Some days, your body ♪
♪ Has to carry on ♪
♪ So you gotta show ♪
♪ A little backbone ♪
>> ♪ Ooh-ooh-whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
>> ♪ You know ♪
>> ♪ Ooh-ooh-whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
>> ♪ You know ♪
>> ♪ Ooh-ooh-whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
>> ♪ You know, you know ♪
>> ♪ You gotta show ♪
♪ A little backbone ♪
>> ♪ Ooh-ooh-whoo-ooh ♪
>> ♪ You gotta show ♪
>> ♪ You know ♪
>> ♪ Ooh-ooh-whoo-ooh ♪
>> ♪ You gotta show ♪
>> ♪ Yeah, you know ♪
♪ You gotta show ♪
♪ A little backbone ♪
♪ Are you strong enough ♪
♪ To get back up? ♪
♪ When the chains ♪
♪ Hold you to the ground, yeah ♪
♪ So let's break 'em down ♪
♪ Yeah, uh ♪
♪ Let's break 'em down ♪
>> ♪ Ooh-ooh-whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
>> ♪ You know ♪
>> ♪ Let's break 'em down ♪
>> ♪ Ooh-ooh-whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
>> ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh, I'm telling you ♪
♪ We all fall on hard times ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ Each day is a hard climb ♪
♪ Some days, your body ♪
♪ Has to carry on ♪
♪ So you gotta show a little ♪