>> Announcer: It's the 4th
of July, and Kelly and Ryan
are having a party--
a pool party.
Today here to splash
in the pretend water,
the guys from "Stranger Things."
And you can't have a celebration
without music, so O.A.R. is here
as our holiday house band.
And the co-hosts are tossing
bags with the American Cornhole
champions.
Plus, members of our
studio audience could win
some holiday prizes when they
compete in our 4th of July Games
all next on "Live."
[upbeat music]ive."
♪ ♪
And now here are your
all-American co-hosts,
Kelly Ripa and Ryan Seacrest.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
>> Ryan: Hey!
Whoo!
How's it going?
Hi.
>> Kelly: Hi.
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: Happy 4th of July.
Good morning, everybody.
[cheers and applause]
Welcome to our party.
>> Kelly: Hey, guess what.
O.A.R. is our house band today.
>> Ryan: Yeah, yeah.
>> Kelly: They're gonna be
performing for us throughout
the show.
Thank you.
>> Ryan: Kelly, please.
>> Kelly: Look at this.
>> Ryan: Let's talk about
the 4th of July, Kelly.
>> Kelly: Ryan, I was hoping
you would bring it up.
[laughter]
>> Ryan: The most important part
of the 4th, obviously,
is not necessarily the history
but posting photographs of your
celebration on this day, right?
>> Kelly: Correct.
>> Ryan: So many great
opportunities.
>> Kelly: Correct.
>> Ryan: Now--
>> Kelly: Sophia,
you are so cute.
Sorry, go ahead.
>> Ryan: These are the best
captions for 4th of July
for your pictures.
So you're welcome.
Put these to good use later.
"Drinkin'--
#DrinkinLikeLincoln.
[laughter and cheers]
I'm not making these up.
These are actually online.
Um...
Red, white, and brew.
#RedWhiteAndBrew.
[cheers and applause]
The Star-Spangled Hammered.
>> Kelly: [laughs]
>> Ryan: Sippin' on liber-tea.
>> Kelly: Yeah, I like that.
>> Ryan:, Well, that's--
if you want--
>> Kelly: Mm-hmm.
You know what?
>> Ryan: Tell me, Kel.
>> Kelly: It's funny.
>> Ryan: Is it?
>> Kelly: We're talking about
where can we keep
this gigantic flamingo,
because we can all agree
this is probably the greatest
pool float in the universe.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: I think so.
>> Kelly: Seaworthy.
This is like the yacht
of sea--of pool floats,
would you not say?
>> Ryan: This is it.
This is what you strive for.
>> Kelly: You guys
are rock stars.
You have this all day long.
This is, like, in your tub.
>> Ryan: [laughs]
>> Kelly: But would you like
to see the world's largest pool?
It's at a resort in Chile.
>> Ryan: Look at that.
Oh, my God.
>> Kelly: It's the San Alfonso
del Mar, world's largest
manmade lagoon.
It's the exact same
crystal-clear turquoise hue
of the sea.
So they made the pool look
just like the sea, and they
filled it with seawater.
I mean, why not just go
in the sea, right?
I mean, am I right,
or am I just being a killjoy?
>> Ryan: A lot of people
are afraid of, I don't know,
what they have in the sea.
They could have jellyfish.
They could have other animals,
creatures--
>> Kelly: Well, listen.
Somebody goes over there
and grabs something over there
and pulls a prank
and throws it in the pool,
it's gonna live, because
it's seawater, right?
>> Ryan: "Honey, I'll be
right back.
I'm going to do some laps."
How long you think
that would take, days?
>> Kelly: I guess.
I mean, they've got sailboats
in there!
But we could definitely get a
whole flock of these flamingos.
>> Ryan: Yeah.
We could Jet Ski in there,
if that's legal.
>> Kelly: I see all kinds
of things in there.
>> Ryan: By the way, you know,
there are some people who are
afraid to swim in the ocean,
and so that's a good
alternative.
On the 4th of July,
we should tell you--
I mean, you know this,
obviously, from history--
the United States observes
a federal holiday in honor of
the Declaration of Independence,
commemorates the adoption of
the Declaration of Independence
July 4, 1776...
[cheers and applause]
By delegates from
the 13 colonies.
Now--now the important stuff.
If the 4th of July falls
on a Sunday, we observe
the holiday on the following
Monday.
If it falls on a Saturday,
we observe it on a Friday.
>> Both: If it falls on a...
>> Kelly: On a Tuesday, we take
the whole rest of the week off.
>> Ryan: Exactly.
If it falls in between...
[applause]
>> Kelly: Hey, did you hear
about this?
>> Ryan: No, but I'm about to.
>> Kelly: You guys know--
how many--let's see.
I see a lot of young people here
today.
Millennials and Gen Zers,
>> Ryan: Hey, guys.
>> Kelly: Where are you? Yes?
[cheers and applause]
Lots.
>> Ryan: My people.
>> Kelly: Your people are here.
Your people are representing.
>> Ryan: I see you.
>> Kelly: So the flamingo pose
is the latest Instagram-friendly
stance.
Do you know about the
flamingo pose, everybody?
Here's, I believe--
is that Kendall Jenner?
Yeah, Kendall Jenner is...
well, are they calling it
the flamingo pose because she's
wearing that dress
or because her legs--
the one leg?
>> Ryan: Well, the dress helps.
>> Kelly: Gelman, we are--
you know, we are
in our thong shorts.
>> Gelman: Yes.
>> Kelly: So maybe you can do
the flamingo for us?
Somehow, that looks different.
That doesn't look like--
[laughter]
>> Ryan: That was tree
from yoga.
>> Kelly: You stand on one leg,
and you get bonus points
if you can slightly cross
your knees, which helps
to create a slimming effect
for your legs.
>> Ryan: Let's see
your bonus points.
>> Kelly: Gelman, you've got--
>> Gelman: I broke my knee.
Come on!
What do you want from me?
>> Ryan: The other thing
that's a trend this summer--
this is not good for your skin,
can't highly recommend it--
but they're saying
sunburn tattoos.
You know when you fall asleep
in the sun and you leave
your hand like this?
>> Kelly: Yeah!
>> Ryan: So sunburn tattoos
are big for the summer of 2019.
People are placing stencils
on exposed skin, soaking up
the sun, and then they've got,
you know, the Batman logo
or other different things
that look like a tattoo.
>> Kelly: Oh, that seems
dangerous, though.
>> Ryan: Well, that's not great.
>> Kelly: It's not--here's
the thing, kids,
and I'm gonna tell you this.
[clears throat]
[sighs] Oh, gosh.
Here's what I'm gonna tell you,
because nobody told us,
in my day, this, because
there was still, like, a lot
of conflicting data
about sunscreen,
at least in our household.
>> Ryan: Right.
>> Kelly: It's not the sunburn
that day, right?
It's what that sunburn
turns into 30 years from now.
Right, moms?
Yeah.
>> Ryan: So put it on early so--
>> Kelly: And I know
that it is in your instinct,
Sophia, to tune out the moms.
Do you understand?
I get it.
I--we get it.
It's everybody's instinct
to tune out the moms.
>> Ryan: Right.
>> Kelly: But we actually--
and this--we actually,
when it comes to this thing,
know exactly what we're
talking about.
>> Ryan: You carry wisdom
with this.
>> Kelly: Yes.
You don't need--you don't need
a Batman-shaped melanoma
30 years from now.
[laughter and applause]
>> Ryan: One other quick
public service
for the barbecuers today,
for July 4th.
>> Kelly: Yes?
>> Ryan: If you are someone
that tends--like, when I'm out
and I'm with other people,
usually they get
the mosquito bites.
>> Kelly: Am I crowding you?
I just noticed you leaned away
from me.
I feel like--I feel like
I just brushed my teeth,
so I don't think it's--
>> Ryan: No, no, no,
you smell like a lozenge.
>> Kelly: I do.
Well, that's because I ate
the lozenge.
>> Ryan: No, but you're not
crowding me at all.
>> Kelly: Right.
>> Ryan: I just wanted
to make eye contact.
>> Kelly: Oh, okay.
So your--
so your vision is going.
>> Ryan: My vision's bad.
Kelly?
>> Kelly: Okay.
>> Ryan: Kelly?
>> Kelly: You're the first
Millennial I've ever seen
do that.
>> Ryan: Can I borrow
my Millennial glasses
to read this?
>> Kelly: Sure, go for it.
>> Ryan: Oh, look at this.
No, it's a public service.
So usually I'm not the one
that gets eaten by mosquitoes.
It's the person I'm with, which
is a great going-out benefit.
>> Kelly: Oh, my gosh.
>> Ryan: But if you're the one
that always gets the mosquito
bites, researchers say
music by Skrillex will prevent
the mosquitoes from biting you.
>> Gelman: [laughs]
>> Ryan: Researchers examined
the effects of electronic music
on mosquitoes, and it made them
less likely to bite.
>> Kelly: Yay, Skrillex.
>> Ryan: So Skrillex is the
soundtrack to your barbecue.
Today on the show, the cast
of "Stranger Things,"
they are here.
Gaten, Finn, Caleb, Noah--
they're all here backstage,
a whole bunch of them.
>> Kelly: And nothing says
4th of July like cornhole,
so we're gonna play cornhole
with the top competitors from
the American Cornhole League.
By the way...
[applause]
I was like, "I thought
we called it, on our show,
Live Hole," and they were
like, "No, it's only Live Hole
when we throw the beanbags
into our mouths."
>> Gelman: Exactly.
We've a special game
that we've developed.
>> Kelly: Unbelievable.
>> Gelman: This is
the real game.
>> Ryan: This is the real--
>> Kelly: This is the real...
>> Ryan: This is the league.
>> Kelly: Cornhole.
>> Ryan: We have the league
champions, all right.
And throughout today's show,
members of our studio audience
will play "Live's"
4th of July Games.
The first game is our annual
4th of July Trivia
Dancer Off.
The dancers
dressed themselves up.
They're ready to try and dance
their way to victory.
So let's dance!
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: First up, say hello
to Mary Malloy
from East Rockaway, New York.
[upbeat music]
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: Our next contestant
is Gary Callioni
from Cincinnati, Ohio.
Gare.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
What's up, my brother?
>> Kelly: Nice, Gary.
Our third contestant is
Carla Gomen from
El Dorado Hills, California.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
Very nice.
>> Ryan: And last but not least,
let's bring out Meredith Miller
from San Antonio, Texas.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
>> Kelly: All right,
studio audience.
You have a job.
>> Ryan: Oh, yes.
>> Kelly: You're going to vote
for your favorite dancer,
and after trivia we will
announce who the audience picked
to win, okay?
>> Ryan: All right, now...
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: So uncomf--
>> Ryan: These are cool.
>> Kelly: Thanks.
>> Ryan: I love those.
>> Kelly: They're not mine;
they're Jan's.
>> Ryan: Oh, well, Jan,
those are great.
>> Kelly: Thank you.
>> Ryan: All week long, we're
playing a special audience
edition of Stump the Hosts,
where an audience member shares
a summer-themed truth or lie
and we have to figure out
which is verdad.
>> Kelly: If they stump us,
they get a Kelly and Ryan mug
and $1,200 kitchen appliance
package from Cuisinart...
[cheers and applause]
Which we can all agree is
all of the kitchen appliances.
>> Ryan: It is everything.
So, dancers, give it your all
right now.
It's time for Stump the Hosts
audience edition.
[Lady Gaga's "Just Dance"]
>> ♪ Just dance ♪
♪ Gonna be okay ♪
♪ Da da doo-doo-mm ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
♪ Spin that record, babe ♪
♪ Da da doo-doo-mm ♪
♪ Just dance ♪
♪ Gonna be okay ♪
♪ J-j-just dance ♪
>> ♪ Gonna be okay ♪
>> ♪ Dance dance ♪
>> Whoo!
>> ♪ J-j-just dance ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ Half psychotic, sick ♪
♪ Hypnotic ♪
♪ Got my blueprint ♪
♪ Half psychotic, sick ♪
♪ Hypnotic ♪
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: All right, okay.
>> Kelly: Now, that's
what I call U.S. of Yay.
Am I right?
Yeah, that's right.
>> Ryan: Happy Independence Day.
>> Kelly: Good job, you four.
Amazing.
Now let's meet today's
audience participant.
Where is Holly Dance
from Ogden, Utah?
>> Ryan: Holly Dance?
>> Kelly: Hi, Holly!
[cheers and applause]
Okay.
>> Ryan: Okay.
>> Kelly: Okay, you can stay
right there in the ocean,
and Ryan and I will stay here
on this side of the--
tail end of the flamingo.
>> Awesome.
>> Ryan: So by the way,
happy 4th of July.
>> Thank you so much!
>> Ryan: You look great.
>> Thank you.
>> Kelly: You look adorable.
>> Ryan: What is your first
statement?
>> My first statement
is that every summer,
my family and I, we have
a friend who's in marketing,
and we get a billboard,
a vinyl billboard,
rip the whole thing down,
put it down the hill
in their backyard, and we
waterslide down the billboard.
>> Ryan: Oh!
>> Kelly: Oh, that sounds
like fun.
>> Ryan: Do you steal
the billboard from--
>> No, he's in marketing,
so they're old billboards.
>> Ryan: They're old,
so it's fine.
Okay, and what's your second
statement?
>> My second statement is that
every 4th of July,
my husband and I are in
the town parade, and we're
a husband-and-wife
real estate team, so I dress up
as the Statue of Liberty,
and we have a big American flag,
and we throw out candy
in the parade.
>> Ryan: But he's in marketing,
I thought.
>> No, a friend is in marketing.
>> Ryan: Oh.
Let's see what the audience
thinks on this.
>> Kelly: You've got
an honest face.
>> Ryan: You do.
Sliding down the vinyl
billboard.
>> Kelly: Huh.
>> Ryan: So you put water on it.
>> Yeah, we get a hose
and put it at the top.
>> Ryan: Do you soap, like--
>> Yup, we get dish soap
at the top, and the kids all
squirt it down--
>> Kelly: That sounds dangerous,
like you could really
hurt yourself.
>> Ryan: That sounds fun.
>> Kelly: Even on the
Slip 'n Slide, right?
>> It's a grass hill.
>> Kelly: Adults over the age
of 12 and if you weigh more
than blah, blah, blah...
>> It's a grass hill.
>> Ryan: It's a grass hill.
I--I like that story.
What do you think?
>> Kelly: I think that that's--
okay, I'm gonna--I don't want
to--it's the 4th of July,
so for the sake of harmony,
I'm gonna go with you,
but in the back of my mind,
I want it noted that I actually
believe that is BS, okay?
[laughter]
>> Ryan: In the name of harmony,
is it true that you slide
down the billboard?
>> Am I supposed to tell you
right now?
>> Ryan: Yes, right now.
>> Yes, it's true.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: Happy holiday.
>> Kelly: Wow.
>> Ryan: Thank you, audience.
Thank you.
>> Yeah.
>> Kelly: Now you and a lucky
member of our studio audience
will each receive a $500
gift card from World Market.
>> [shrieks]
Yeah!
4th of July!
>> Ryan: Fishbowl.
>> Kelly: Huh?
>> Ryan: Right here.
>> Kelly: Oh, fishbowl.
Yeah, sorry.
>> Ryan: We've got your tickets,
everybody.
>> Kelly: There's nothing like
doing this show
like it's the first time...
>> Ryan: We've ever done it.
>> Kelly: Even though
it's my 9,000th show.
Uh, 40, number 40.
>> Ryan: Number 40?
>> Yeah!
>> Ryan: Right there?
>> Whoo!
>> Ryan: Happy 4th.
Thank you so much
for being here.
>> Kelly: Thank you very much.
Thanks.
>> Ryan: Let's see.
Now dim the lights, because--
>> Kelly: Oh, is this where
we reveal the winning dancer?
>> Ryan: The results...
>> Kelly: Oh, my gosh.
>> Ryan: Of our dance-off
are in.
The person voted
as this year's winner
and getting a $500
gift certificate to Omaha Steaks
is...
We'll find out after the break.
[groans and laughter]
>> Kelly: [laughs]
Just kidding.
Calm down.
>> Ryan: It is Carla!
Carla from El Dorado Hills,
California.
[cheers and applause]
Good job, Carla!
>> Kelly: That's good sportsmen.
Thank you for playing,
and happy 4th of July.
>> Ryan: Coming up next,
the cast of "Stranger Things."
We're right back on the 4th.
Just whatever.
>> Kelly: I know; I was like...
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
>> Announcer: Still ahead
on "Live," O.A.R. will perform
their latest hit.
We'll continue to celebrate
Independence Day
with 4th of July games,
when more lucky members
of our studio audience
will win more prizes.
We'll play cornhole
with the league champions.
Coming up next, the cast
of "Stranger Things."
♪ ♪
[electronic noises]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
>> [whispers] Now.
[toys wind down]
[horns blaring]
>> [screaming]
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: You're scared already.
Here come four of the young
residents of the twisted
television town
of Hawkins, Indiana.
From the hit series
"Stranger Things," please
welcome Finn Wolfhard,
Noah Schnapp, Caleb McLaughlin,
and Gaten Matarazzo!
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat rock music]
♪ ♪
Hi.
Come on in.
>> Ryan: Come on in.
What's up, bro?
>> Kelly: Hi, Finn.
How are you?
Welcome, welcome.
Come on in.
Hi.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: Come on in.
>> Kelly: Hi.
We've never met before.
Hi, I'm Kelly.
>> Ryan: All right!
>> Kelly: Hi, baby, how are you?
Good to see you too.
[indistinct chatter]
>> Where are we going into?
>> Kelly: Sit on the cushions
there.
>> Ryan: Yeah, a celebration.
>> Kelly: This shouldn't be
awkward at all.
>> No.
>> It's actually quite comfy.
>> Yeah.
>> Ryan: Isn't it nice?
>> Kelly: What do you think
of this?
Now, you guys--listen, you guys
are Hollywood stars.
You must have these
falling out of the sky.
>> Ryan: That's right.
>> Yeah, it's on our rider.
>> Ryan: So where is everyone
from?
Let's see.
>> I'm from New York City,
the Big Apple.
>> Ryan: You're from
the Big Apple, okay.
>> Kelly: New York City!
Born and raised?
>> Yes, born and raised.
>> Kelly: All right.
>> Ryan: And Finn's from
Vancouver, right?
>> I'm from Vancouver.
>> Kelly: What about you?
>> I'm from--my whole family
is from Montreal,
but I'm from New York.
>> Kelly: Oh, okay, fab.
>> Jersey.
>> Kelly: Come on.
>> Ryan: Oh, there you go.
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: I don't want to show
favorites.
I'm just saying--
>> I understand.
>> Kelly: People from Jersey
understand each other.
That's all I'm saying.
>> New York is better,
but it's okay.
[people talking at once]
>> Our families are all from
Canada, so we're nicer.
>> Kelly: Oh, you're more
polite.
You're more polite.
>> Ryan: Now that you guys
have worked together
for a few seasons, I'm sure
you get to know each other.
Like, I know what--can't get
under her skin, but I know
what can wind Kelly up, right?
>> Kelly: What's one thing
that can wind me up?
>> Ryan: Serving you garlic.
>> Kelly: Oh, that is true.
>> Ryan: If you put garlic
in any of her food--
>> I love garlic.
>> Kelly: You do?
>> Ryan: I love it too.
She doesn't love it.
>> Kelly: I'm very sensitive
to it.
>> Oh.
>> Ryan: So do you guys know
little things
about each other now?
>> I thought you were about
to ask us if we knew anything
about garlic.
>> Kelly: [laughs]
>> "Well..."
>> Caleb's always blowing
his nose, all the time.
>> Kelly: Oh, really?
>> Every day of his life.
>> You know why?
I have PTSD as a child.
>> Kelly: Okay.
>> I look at old pictures
of my young self, and there's
a lot of boogers, so I--
[laughter]
So I suffer from that,
and I'm like--I make sure there
is no boogers in my nose, so--
>> Kelly: Wait, do you have,
like, older siblings?
>> Yeah, I do,
but they won't tell me.
>> Kelly: They didn't tell you.
That's right, yeah.
>> Ryan: Well, you should have
people on the set that tell you
whether--
>> Oh, they do, but I just--
when I feel something, I'm like,
"Can I get a tissue?"
It's not there.
>> Kelly: Kelly loves
the snot rocket.
She just fires it right out.
>> Well, it comes to the point
where it's like we're doing
a really serious scene,
and Caleb's off camera,
and I'm doing the scene.
I look at Caleb, and he's like:
[imitates blowing nose]
>> Kelly: [laughs]
>> As quietly as you can.
>> Every picture of myself
as a three-year-old child,
it's just shiny boogers.
>> But that's with every kid.
>> I know.
>> We've been doing scenes,
and, like, the camera will be
on one of us, and he'll be
behind the camera, reading
for us, and he'll just be
blowing his nose
during the middle of the shot.
I'm like, "Dude, really?"
>> And it makes you laugh
so much.
>> Ryan: Well, what does
Gaten do?
What does Gaten do?
>> Kelly: He's perfect;
he's from New Jersey.
>> Gaten does, like--
>> Yeah, Gaten does a lot.
>> He dances and sings a lot.
>> Kelly: Well, 'cause he's
happy.
He's from New Jersey.
[overlapping chatter]
>> Are all people
from New Jersey happy?
>> Kelly: Yes, we're all--
>> No!
Oh, God, no.
>> Kelly: We are happy,
and if you question us,
we will fight you about it.
Yeah, that's right.
>> That's how happy we are.
>> Kelly: That's right.
>> We will beat you up
over how happy we are.
>> Ryan: Who has their
driver's license among you?
>> No one has it.
>> Good question.
>> I'm at permit.
>> Ryan: You're permitting?
>> Yeah, I get my license
in September.
>> Kelly: Oh, you do, okay.
>> I get my license
when I turn 18.
>> Kelly: When you turn 18.
>> Yeah, this year, this year.
>> [laughs]
He was always bragging about--
>> Yeah, I can get go-karts.
I got--I went in for the first
learner's permit test,
really excited, and I got--
I didn't get every question
wrong, but...
>> Ryan: [laughs]
>> It's why I chose acting
over academics, and...
>> Ryan: [laughs] Oh, God.
>> I got one question wrong.
It was, like, the passing thing,
and, like, just held my head low
when I got out.
My mom was like, "Did you pass?"
And I was just like, "Let's go."
>> Kelly: You know what?
You guys, get chauffeurs.
You're on a hit show,
for God's sake.
>> I want to drive.
>> We got to drive.
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: Yeah.
>> Is everyone a chauffeur
in the audience?
We got a chauffer's audience.
>> Now that I'm finally driving,
I don't like being a passenger
at all.
>> Ryan: 'Cause you want to be
in control.
>> Backseat driver?
>> I'm not a backseat driver.
I try not to be, but...
It was funny.
My uncle, my mom's twin brother,
told her when she first started
driving--'cause he got
his license first--that if
there was a white line
around the stop sign,
it was optional.
>> Ryan: What?
[laughter]
>> Kelly: That's really funny.
>> And for those of you
who don't know--I'm sure
most of you do--most stop signs
have a white line around them.
And it took her, like,
three months to realize
that was not true.
>> So how many stop signs--
>> And no one was hurt.
No one was hurt.
Everyone was fine.
>> Kelly: Nobody was hurt.
I love that.
>> Ryan: So you guys are on
this massively popular show,
"Stranger Things."
>> I'm falling.
>> Ryan: That's all right;
there's a hole there.
>> Kelly: There's a hole,
we've decided.
Just lean back and relax.
>> Ryan: Is it difficult
to keep the secrets
of the show?
'Cause people are always wanting
to know what's coming up,
what's happening, right?
>> I feel like now it is,
because we're in season three.
In the beginning it wasn't
so hard, because nothing
was out.
But now I'm forgetting
which season I'm talking about.
>> Yes.
>> And then I might spoil
something or say something about
the season that's coming out.
But no one catches it.
>> In season one,
we told everyone, like,
the entire plotline.
I was spoiling everything.
>> We were like, "Okay,
so there's this girl named
Eleven, and then at the end,
she disappears."
>> Kelly: And everybody's like,
"Good show."
[overlapping chatter]
>> Yeah, and then we were like,
"Yeah, that was probably it."
>> Kelly: But you do realize
that you are portraying
the greatest time
in the history of time,
the '80s.
>> Yeah.
Like, our parents are always
telling us how they love it.
>> Kelly: Your parents
are literally telling you
what it was like during--
>> Yeah, my parents relate
to everything--like, the towels
that we have and--or not
the towels.
Our shirts have, like,
towel material.
>> Kelly: Yes, of course.
>> Terrycloth.
>> Kelly: Terrycloth.
>> They wore that.
>> Kelly: "Towel material."
>> Ryan: Towel material.
>> Kelly: That was adorable.
My kids, for the first time,
saw a wall phone
on "Stranger Things,"
and they said, "What is
that thing?"
They'd never seen a wall phone.
>> There's, like, a whole bunch
in New York City.
>> Kelly: Okay, I doubt,
before you did
"Stranger Things,"
if you really think back--
>> Ryan: Hey, Jersey!
Calm down, you two.
>> I knew
what a rotary phone was.
>> Ryan: We're gonna take
a break.
Coming up, things get stranger
when the guys play
a hands-on guessing game
right after this.
Stay with us.
[upbeat band music]
♪ ♪
>> Announcer: Still ahead
on "Live," a performance
by house band O.A.R.
♪ ♪
[playing "Ring of Fire"]
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: "Stranger Things."
"Stranger Things 3" available
today on Netflix.
Today, today, today.
>> Ryan: Today's the day.
>> Kelly: I'm sure people have
already binged the entire season
while we sat here on the show,
but we are back with the cast
of "Stranger Things,"
and everybody here is gonna
participate in a game
of What's in the Box?
[applause]
For this challenge,
Ryan and the boys are gonna
reach into these boxes here
and guess what strange thing
they think they're feeling.
I am the only one that has
the answers right here
and will reveal
what's in each box.
Are you fellas ready?
>> Wait, so you know
what's in the box?
>> Kelly: Yes, I know
what's in the box.
>> Ryan: We do not.
>> Kelly: It is disgusting.
>> Here we go. One...
>> Both: Two, three.
>> Kelly: Do it.
>> Oh, my God, it's oatmeal!
It's oatmeal.
>> Ryan: Feels like oatmeal.
>> That's oatmeal.
>> Kelly: You are incorrect!
It is relish.
>> I knew it was relish!
I smelled it.
>> Ryan: Gross!
>> I didn't even say my answer.
>> Kelly: Next!
>> Ryan: Next one, next one,
next one.
>> So you just put your hand
into relish for no reason.
I didn't.
>> You didn't put your hand in
for the relish?
>> Wait, you didn't put
your hand in?
That's so unfair.
>> Kelly: Finn is a thinker.
See this?
He's like, "I'm not putting
my hand in."
>> I double-crossed everyone.
>> Ryan: Let's go. Next one.
>> Kelly: Okay.
Next one.
On your mark.
Get set. Go.
>> Jell-O!
>> Kelly: You are correct.
Yes, Jell-O.
>> Oh, yeah, that feels so good.
>> That feels so good.
>> Ryan: Doesn't feel as gross
as the relish.
>> Ew, dude, don't eat it.
>> It's Jell-O!
>> Kelly: It's Jell-O.
It's Jell-O.
>> It's like relish Jell-O.
>> We don't have to wipe
our hands.
>> Kelly: Did it taste
a little bit like relish?
>> Like Jell-O.
>> Kelly: Jell-O.
Okay, good.
>> Ryan: Next one?
>> Kelly: Next one,
number three.
>> Marshmallow fluff.
>> Oh, it's marsh--
>> No.
>> Oh, oh.
>> Shaving cream.
>> Kelly: Yes!
>> It smells like shaving cream.
>> Kelly: You are correct.
Shaving cream.
>> High five, high five.
[applause]
>> Kelly: You still have relish
on your hands.
>> Noah!
>> That smells so good.
>> It's so tempting.
>> It smells so good.
>> Kelly: You guys--
>> Ryan: All right, next one?
>> Try me.
>> All right, cool.
>> Ryan: Get in there.
>> Kelly: You know what?
Finn the Canadian could be
my favorite new player
of this game.
>> "Finn the Canadian."
>> Why?
>> Kelly: Finn, have you put
your hands in anything yet?
Oh, you did.
Okay, all right.
I thought for sure
it was three for three.
Okay, next one.
Next one.
>> Feels so nice.
>> Okay.
>> Kelly: Okay, do it.
>> Ryan: This feels great.
Worms.
>> Oh, worm--gummy worms.
>> Um, n--it's a gummy worm,
right?
>> Kelly: Yeah, they are
gummy worms.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: I felt worms
on the show before.
>> Kelly: I just want to say
one thing.
Ryan is cheating.
>> Why are they wet?
>> Ryan: So they feel like
real worms.
>> Oh!
>> Kelly: Ryan, you're not
allowed to pull it out
of the thing.
>> Ryan!
>> Ryan: Now you tell me.
>> Kelly: Just telling you.
Those are the rules.
>> Ryan: I didn't hear that
in the rules.
>> Oh, my God.
>> Kelly: This is
for all the marbles.
>> Ryan: Let's get
to the next box.
I won't pull it out.
>> Kelly: This is
for all the marbles.
>> Ryan: High five, high five,
high five, partner.
All right, next one.
>> Kelly: Wait, Finn,
what is it?
All you got from this is what?
>> Clean hands.
>> Kelly: Clean hands.
>> Ryan: And a clean shave.
>> Yeah, I'm--yeah.
>> Kelly: Okay, guys, this is
the final one, and this one is--
you earn your--
>> No!
>> Kelly: Do it.
>> What is it?
>> Kelly: I don't know.
What do you think it is?
>> Noah, no, wait, not yet.
>> Oh, I thought we were--
>> Kelly: What do you think
it is?
>> Ryan: Feels like
an intestine.
>> I don't want to know
what that is.
>> Oh, my God, meatballs!
>> Is it meat?
>> Is it chicken?
>> Is it manure?
>> Ground beef?
>> Kelly: It's not manure.
>> Is it--
>> Is it liver?
>> I feel it!
>> It's ground beef.
It's ground beef.
>> Kelly: It's not ground beef.
>> Ryan: All right,
we're out of guesses.
>> Steak?
>> Kelly: It's not snake.
>> Steak.
>> Kelly: Oh.
No, it's wet hot dog buns.
[audience groans]
>> Ew.
>> Kelly: You're welcome,
everybody.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: You guys
are good sports.
High five, high five, high five,
high five.
>> Oh!
>> Kelly: Gentlemen.
[all talking at once]
I'm proud to present you
with these incredible trophies.
>> Ryan: Each of you are
winners.
>> Ah!
>> Ryan: Thanks, guys.
Congratulations on season three.
>> Kelly: You're all winners.
>> We all won?
>> I didn't guess any of them.
>> Kelly: Hey, Ryan, guess what.
>> Ryan: Oh, I get one too?
>> Kelly: You win a prize too,
Ry.
All right!
>> Ryan: No one goes home
empty-handed.
>> Kelly: Hey, Finn Wolfhard,
Noah Schnapp, Caleb McLaughlin,
and Gaten Matarazzo,
the stars of "Stranger Things"!
>> Ryan: Well done, guys.
Well done.
[cheers and applause]
We'll be right back!
["Ring of Fire" playing]
♪ ♪
>> Announcer: Tomorrow on
"Live," Ricky Gervais.
♪ ♪
>> Announcer: If your grilling's
got game and you have a dish
that inspires high praise,
then you'd be perfect for our
Grillin'spiration
summer cook-off.
Tell us about your dish,
and you might have a chance
to come here to inspire everyone
at home to get cookin'.
Submit your recipe
and a short video telling us
all about what makes your dish
so popular.
And let's add a little
Grillin'spiration to the summer.
Go to KellyandRyan.com
to find out more details
on how to enter.
>> ♪ Smile ♪
♪ Babe, we only here ♪
♪ Oh, for a little while ♪
♪ ♪
>> Ryan: O.A.R. right there.
>> Kelly: It's amazing.
I love having O.A.R. here
as our house band.
It's amazing.
Thank you, guys.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: Our 4th of July
games continue.
For this challenge,
we have each partnered
with an audience member.
My teammate is Sarah Hollis
from Edmond, Oklahoma.
Good to meet you.
>> Kelly: And my winning partner
is Victoria Stutzman
from Elsie, Michigan.
And in this game,
what do we have?
60 seconds...
>> Ryan: 60 seconds, yeah.
>> Kelly: To find red and blue
necklaces.
>> Ryan: Blue for us,
red for you.
>> Kelly: Yes, red for us.
We have to put them
on our necks, right?
>> Ryan: Correct.
>> Kelly: We cannot--we're not
allowed to sabotage
the other team by throwing
their colors out of the--
>> Ryan: Did you hear that?
You're not allowed to sabotage
the other team.
>> Kelly: Did you hear it?
You're not allowed to sabotage
the other team.
>> Ryan: Okay, fine.
All right, here we go, Sarah.
>> Kelly: You know what he's
trying to do?
He's trying to feel around
in the ground.
>> Ryan: I know where they are.
>> Kelly: I'm all over it.
>> Ryan: Okay.
>> Kelly: Okay, now--
>> Ryan: The winner.
>> Kelly: Okay, so Elsie and I
are looking for the red
necklaces.
Ryan and Sarah are looking
for the blue ones.
Once we put them on our necks,
we're gonna find out
who wins, right?
And whoever wins
wins $10 million.
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: The team with the most
combined necklaces
wins a $500 gift card
from Barnes & Noble, okay?
>> Kelly: Which is
the same thing as $10 million.
>> Ryan: Ready?
>> Yes.
>> Ryan: Set.
Go.
[cheers and applause]
>> Oh!
[laughs]
[playful music playing]
♪ ♪
>> Kelly: You are--
you're a monster.
>> Ryan: [laughing]
Hey!
>> Kelly: Freeze you in.
♪ ♪
>> Kelly: [laughs]
>> Ryan: Oh, my God,
I can't find--
♪ ♪
>> [screams]
>> all: Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
[cheers and applause]
[bell rings]
>> Kelly: You know what?
I'm not gonna lie;
that got violent.
[laughs]
>> Ryan: I got all the red ones.
>> Kelly: Whoo!
>> Ryan: Ugh...
>> Gelman: Everyone count
how many they have.
>> Ryan: Okay, well, we need
that one.
All right, count them up, Sarah.
How many do you have?
>> One, two...
>> Ryan: This was much easier
as a kid.
>> Three...
>> Kelly: This one doesn't
count?
>> Ryan: Four.
>> Oh, gosh.
>> Ryan: That's disqualified.
>> Kelly: The red one counts,
but the blue one doesn't.
>> Five, six.
>> Both: Seven, eight, nine,
ten...
>> 11!
>> Ryan: 11, okay.
11 blues.
>> Kelly: 1, 2, 3...
4, 5, 6...
>> 7, 8, 9, 10...
11, 12...
>> Kelly: Ryan!
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: I got none.
>> How?
>> Kelly: Sorry, sorry.
>> Ryan: I didn't get one.
>> Kelly: It got--
I'm not gonna lie.
Ryan and I full-on punched
each other.
[laughs]
>> Ryan: All right, Sarah,
thank you so much.
>> Kelly: There was
hair removal.
>> Ryan: There was all kinds
of going on.
We'll be right back
with cornhole after the break.
>> Kelly: Whoo-hoo!
>> Ryan: Oh, my God.
>> ♪ I just wanna ♪
♪ Make you laugh ♪
♪ I just wanna see that smile ♪
>> Announcer: Monday on "Live,"
wrestler-turned-actor
Dave Bautista.
>> ♪ For a little while ♪
♪ I just want to hold you till ♪
♪ You fall asleep ♪
♪ I want love, I want us ♪
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
>> Ryan: Well, well, well.
We've recovered from that,
and we're back.
>> Kelly: How do you feel?
Are you okay?
>> Ryan: I'm sore.
I'm bruised.
I was strangled.
>> Kelly: Aw!
>> Ryan: I mean, Gelman,
lots of illegal moves there.
I've watched the tape
in the break.
>> Kelly: The only move
that I heard that was illegal
was taking your blue necklaces
and throwing them outside
of the ball pit.
>> Ryan: That's--that's right,
cheater.
>> Kelly: That's right.
It wouldn't be a 4th of July
party without a fun game
of cornhole.
>> Ryan: All right.
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: Today the highest
ranked players will be competing
against each other at the
national cornhole championship.
>> Ryan: We have the top male
and top female competitors
from the American Cornhole
League here today.
Please welcome Cody Henderson
and Stacia Pugh.
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
>> Kelly: Yeah!
>> Ryan: How are you?
>> Good. How are you?
>> Kelly: Hi, Cody.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Kelly: Hi, Stacia.
I'm Kelly.
Nice to meet you.
>> Ryan: Good to see you.
Come on--come over here.
There you go, okay.
>> Kelly: Cody, you are
27 years old.
How did you get into competitive
cornholing?
>> I got in in high school.
It was just a game
I liked to have fun.
I found the professional
circuit.
And for the last eight years,,
I've been playing competitively,
traveling around the country,
and it's been quite
the experience.
>> Ryan: And, Stacia,
how about for you?
>> For me, I've been playing
about ten years.
Kind of started in the
front yard with my dad,
you know, at family events.
And just realized I liked
the game and played more
and more.
>> Kelly: Played more and more.
Okay, is there something
we should know?
We're not very good cornholers,
we found out recently,
last 4th of July.
>> Ryan: Embarrassingly, we did.
>> Kelly: Is there a technique?
Is there something
we should know?
Like, is there a twist, a thing?
>> There is.
I mean, you know, when it comes
to cornhole, if you can throw
a flat bag, then you'll beat
90% of people.
>> Kelly: So the bag
should be flat.
>> Yes.
>> Kelly: Okay, got it.
>> Ryan: Wait it's--I don't know
that--what that--just, okay,
like this?
>> Kelly: Flat bag.
>> Ryan: And you go like this?
>> Yes.
>> Well, spin like a pizza.
>> Ryan: Like a pizza.
See, we're getting more tips.
All right, let's play.
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: Girls versus boys.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Kelly: Okay, girls
versus boys.
You ready to lose again?
>> Ryan: Ah, yes.
>> Kelly: Okay.
>> Ryan: Come on.
Let's go down here.
[cheers and applause]
>> So you go on that side.
>> Kelly: Now, am I allowed
to block the--
>> Ryan: No, you can't do
any of that.
>> Kelly: Okay.
Can I hit Ryan for no reason?
>> Ryan: Yes.
>> Kelly: Okay.
[light upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
>> Nice flat spin.
>> Ryan: Good spin,
like a pizza.
>> Yes.
Walk it right up the board.
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
>> all: Oh!
>> Kelly: Okay.
So one got knocked in.
What does that mean?
>> Ryan: It means we got
a big deal.
Yeah, we're tied up there.
>> Kelly: Okay.
>> We call that
a replacement bag.
>> Kelly: A replacement bag.
Okay, got it.
>> Replacement bag.
♪ ♪
Oh!
>> Kelly: Okay, now,
you knocked in his.
Do we get that point?
>> Ryan: No.
♪ ♪
Oh, so close.
>> [sighs]
>> both: Okay, now what?
>> Okay, now you're gonna
throw them back.
>> Kelly: We throw them back.
>> Ryan: All right, does anyone
have the--we calculated this?
>> Yeah, so there's
three points there.
>> Ryan: These are so close,
do we get any for that?
>> No.
No, so it would be one
on the board, three in the hole.
That round was eight on five.
We get three.
So we have a three-point lead.
>> Kelly: You go first, right?
Right, Ry?
>> You'll be on that side.
>> You're across from me.
>> Kelly: Okay, got it.
>> Okay, Ryan, lead us off.
>> Kelly: And don't let any
of this make you nervous.
>> Ryan: I don't think
I can do the pizza thing.
>> Kelly: You can totally do
the pizza.
You love pizza.
>> Ryan: I do,
but I can't do the toss.
>> Kelly: Just try it.
Toss it.
Toss it, Ryan.
[audience cheering]
>> Oh!
[laughter]
>> All right, Kelly.
You got this.
>> Kelly: Learned a lot.
>> Ryan: All right, Kelly.
Okay.
Don't--don't give me
protective arm.
♪ ♪
[audience groans]
>> Ryan: I almost fell
in the pool.
>> Kelly: How far over the plane
is Ryan allowed to step?
>> Ryan: Just not in the water.
>> You could step up
to the board.
>> Kelly: Up to the board.
>> Up to the very front
of the board.
♪ ♪
>> Good try.
>> Kelly: Okay, inching on
up there.
>> Ryan: We're getting there.
♪ ♪
>> Kelly: Aw!
>> Closer, closer.
[audience cheering]
>> Aw!
♪ ♪
>> Kelly: Ooh, Ryan, that was--
it was almost good.
>> Ryan: Not good enough.
Story of my life.
>> Come on, Kelly.
>> Ryan: It's harder
than it looks.
>> all: Oh!
[cheers and applause]
>> Ryan: Thanks so much.
Nice to meet you.
>> Kelly: Sorry, sorry.
I apologize.
>> Ryan: You can see
the national cornhole
championship today, 1:00 p.m.,
on ESPN.
Cody, Stacia, thank you so much.
O.A.R. performs next.
>> Kelly: Stick around.
Sorry about that.
♪ ♪
>> Announcer: Tomorrow
on "Live," reality star
DJ Pauly D.
♪ ♪
>> Ryan: Welcome back.
All right.
They've been house-banding it,
but now we're ready.
O.A.R.'s new album
is available now.
Here they are with a brand-new
hit, "Knocking at Your Door."
O.A.R.
[cheers and applause]
>> ♪ All I know ♪
♪ I've been here before ♪
♪ I longed so long ♪
♪ Miles and miles to shore ♪
♪ 40,000 angels could fly ♪
♪ By me ♪
♪ Oh, please ♪
♪ Carry me through the night ♪
♪ Because I got to go ♪
♪ Not a minute more ♪
♪ I need a miracle ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I'm gonna let you know ♪
♪ That you're not alone ♪
♪ So I'm coming home ♪
>> ♪ And who's knocking ♪
♪ At your door? ♪
♪ It's me coming back ♪
♪ For more ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
♪ I'm not gonna fall away ♪
♪ And time is my enemy ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
♪ Be there ♪
♪ ♪
>> ♪ But I'm moving ♪
♪ All these mountains aside ♪
>> ♪ Moving ♪
♪ All these mountains ♪
>> ♪ No one will fall ♪
♪ While you sleep ♪
♪ Through the night ♪
♪ Because I got to go ♪
♪ Not a minute more ♪
♪ I need a miracle ♪
♪ I'm gonna let you know ♪
♪ That you're not alone ♪
♪ So I'm coming home ♪
>> ♪ And who's knocking ♪
♪ At your door? ♪
♪ It's me coming back ♪
♪ For more ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
♪ I'm not gonna fall away ♪
♪ And time is my enemy ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
>> ♪ On my way, on my way ♪
♪ On my way ♪
♪ And you know ♪
♪ I couldn't wait ♪
♪ Another day ♪
♪ To see your face ♪
♪ Baby, now ♪
>> ♪ I'm on my way, on my way ♪
♪ On my way ♪
>> ♪ And you know ♪
♪ Believe me say ♪
♪ I'm on the way ♪
♪ I'm on my way ♪
>> ♪ Yeah, who's knocking ♪
♪ At your door? ♪
♪ It's me coming back ♪
♪ For more ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
♪ I'm not gonna fall away ♪
♪ And time is my enemy ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
>> ♪ Be there ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ ♪
♪ When you wake up ♪
♪ I'm gonna be there ♪
♪ On my way, on my way ♪
♪ On my way ♪
♪ I'm on my way, on my way ♪
[cheers and applause]
>> Kelly: Come on!
>> Ryan: O.A.R.!
>> Thank you.
>> Kelly: That was amazing.
>> Ryan: Good to see you guys
again.
Good to see you, boys.
>> So good to see you.
>> Kelly: Great to see you.
>> Thank you, as always.
>> Ryan: Great to see you again.
Thanks, guys.
Thank you for house-banding
as well for this--
>> It was our pleasure.
>> Kelly: I got to tell you,
you really, like, brought
the holiday spirit.
It was great.
>> I think you brought--you
brought the holiday spirit.
>> Ryan: It was a team effort.
>> Kelly: We try.
Fantastic.
>> Ryan: O.A.R.'s new album,
it is out now.
Go pick it up.
These guys are the best.
We'll be right back.
>> ♪ On my way ♪
>> Announcer: If you'd like
to know more about anything
you see on "Live,"
just log on to our website at:
KellyandRyan.com.
>> Announcer: Closed captioning
sponsored in part by:
["Red Red Wine" playing]
>> Ryan: One more time.
O.A.R., ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you guys for being here.
>> Kelly: O.A.R., whoo!
>> Ryan: So...
>> Kelly: You know what?
[cheers and applause]
I'm not gonna lie; I think
our barbecue is more fun
than your barbecue.
Whoo!
>> Ryan: U.S. of Yay!
Tomorrow Ricky Gervais is here.
>> Kelly: And DJ Pauly D
is here.
>> Ryan: Have a great holiday.
Whoo!
>> ♪ Red, red wine ♪
♪ Goes to my head ♪
♪ ♪