>> Announcer: IT'S "LIVE WITH
KELLY AND RYAN!"
TODAY, FROM THE NEW FILM
"STUBER," KUMAIL NANJIANI.
PLUS, TELEVISION, FILM, AND
BROADWAY STAR BERNADETTE PETERS.
EVENT DO YOU KNOW THE STORY
ABOUT YOUR DOG?
THEY WILL HELP US FIGURE OUT THE
FACTS.
ALL NEXT ON "LIVE!"
AND NOW, HERE ARE
KELLY RIPA AND RYAN SEACREST!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ryan: THINK YOU ALL VERY
MUCH.
>> Kelly: WE HAVEN'T DONE
ANYTHING YET.
GREAT MINDS THINK ALIKE.
WE'VE BEEN WAITING TWO WEEKS TO
SAY THAT.
>> Ryan: MONDAY, JULY 8TH,
2019.
GOOD MORNING.
>> Kelly: I AM STILL
JET-LAGGED.
I'VE BEEN UP SINCE 3:00 THIS
MORNING.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
>> Ryan: WE ARE ALMOST DONE,
LESS THAN AN HOUR.
>> Kelly: IT'S FUNNY THE OLDER
YOU GET, THE HARDER IT IS TO
FLIP OVER I FEEL LIKE.
>> Ryan: WHEN I GO BACK AND
FORTH EAST TO WEST, I DO THAT
EVERY WEEK.
NOW IT'S PAINFUL BUT YOU ARE ON
THE EUROPEAN JET-LAGGED.
SO IT'S DINNER TIME.
>> Kelly: I'M STARVING.
I WANT TO EAT PASTA RIGHT NOW.
IT WAS GREAT.
CAN I GIVE YOU SOME PHOTOS?
YOU'RE WELCOME.
LET ME JUST SAY THAT WE WENT
HOME TO THE HOUSE WHERE MY
HUSBAND GREW UP AS A SMALL
CHILD, SO WE WENT TO THE HOUSE.
THIS IS NOT HIS BIRTHPLACE
HOUSE.
THIS IS WHERE THEY MOVED WHEN HE
WAS A SMALL KID.
I DON'T KNOW HOW OLD HE IS IN
THIS PHOTO.
I'M GOING TO SAVE FOR OR FIVE
YEARS OLD, THIS IS WHERE THEY
MOVE.
TINY LITTLE BEACH TOWN IN
SOUTHERN ITALY.
THIS ONE OVER HERE IS MY
ADORABLE HUSBAND RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S HIS BROTHER MIKE, AND
THAT'S MY SISTER-IN-LAW.
THERE'S MY MOTHER-IN-LAW RIGHT
THERE, SORRY ABOUT MY
FINGERNAILS, THEY LOOK
RIDICULOUS BUT THESE WERE
VACATION FINGERNAILS.
AND THIS IS MY GRANDFATHER IN
LAW WHO HAS PASSED AWAY IN MAY
HE REST IN PEACE.
SO WE RE-CREATED IT WITH OUR
GROUP, SO THERE WE ARE IN FRONT
OF THE HOUSE, THEY WERE ON THE
INSIDE OF THE FENCE HERE AND WE
ARE ON THE OUTSIDE OF THE FENCE.
RING THE BELL AND NOBODY WAS
HOME.
BUT THERE WE ARE, AND IT WAS
VERY EMOTIONAL TO GO BACK AND TO
HAVE THESE PHOTOS AND TO
PICTURE.
>> Ryan: WHAT WAS MARK'S
REACTION?
>> Kelly: HE WAS VERY
EMOTIONAL.
HE GOES IT'S EXACTLY THE SAME
EXPT THE TRE OTTER.EMEMBE A MINY
WERE LIKE TRULY IN ITALIAN, WHAT
IS IT MEAN ANYMORE BECAUSE WE
LOOK LIKE WE WERE IN THE TRUCK.
AND WE PULLED INTO THE STREET
AND HE GOES EVERYBODY IS GOING
TO COME OUT OF THE FRONT DOOR OR
HANG OVER THE TERRACES.
AND LIKE CLOCKWORK, IT WAS LIKE.
AND IT WAS JUST -- WE STARTED
PLAYING THE GAME, TELL THE NONAS
ON THE TERRACE.
SO I TOOK SOME PICTURES OF MY
HUSBAND BECAUSE I LOVE TO
PHOTOGRAPH HIM ON VACATION.
HE IS SHIRTLESS, YES.
HERE HE IS HERE.
AMERICA AND CANADA, YOU'RE
WELCOME.
AND PLUS, I JUST WANT TO POINT
OUT IN THIS PHOTO, HE IS
SURROUNDED BY MY CHILDREN WHO
WILL NO LONGER LET ME POST
PHOTOS OF THEM.
SO THERE HE IS.
HERE WE ARE, GOT A LITTLE LOST,
HE REFUSED TO ASK FOR
DIRECTIONS, BUT HE THOUGHT HE
COULD JUST FIND IT HIMSELF.
>> Ryan: IT LOOKS LIKE AN AD,
DOESN'T IT?
LIKE A RAY-BAN AD.
I HAD NO IDEA MY PICTURE WAS
BEING TAKEN.
>> Kelly: THERE WE ARE A
MOTHER HE IS WITH MY
DOPPELGAENGER SON OF HIS, LIKE
TWINS.
HERE IS A WALL, AND I FINALLY
SAID TO HIM WILL YOU DO ME A
FAVOR BECAUSE I'M GOING TO SHOW
SOME OF THESE PICTURES ON THE
AIR.
WILL YOU TAKE A PICTURE OF ME?
BECAUSE I JUST WANT TO BE ABLE
TO PROVE THAT I WAS ON THIS TRI
TRIP.
AND SO HE DID, HE TOOK A PICTURE
OF ME.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU CAN SEE IT.
THAT'S ME IF YOU LOOK PAST THE
FLOWERS, THAT'S ME FLOATING ON A
POOL FLOAT.
LIKE A GIANT PILLOW.
THEY CALLED IT A RAVIOLI.
THEY CALL IT THE FLOATING
RAVIOLI.
THAT'S THE ONE PICTURE YOU TOOK
OF ME.
THERE IT IS.
AND THEN I JUST WANTED TO SHOW
YOU SNAKES.
THEY WERE ALSO SNAKES ON THE
TRIP.
THEY WERE FREE, DIDN'T EVEN HAVE
TO PAY EXTRA FOR THE SNAKES.
>> Ryan: YOU SENT ME A TEXT
THAT SAID ONE WORD, SNAKES.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> Kelly: I DON'T KNOW WHY
THEY KEEP FINDING ME.
PEOPLE ARE LIKE THERE ARE NO
SNAKES HERE.
I AM PHOTOGRAPHING SNAKES.
>> Ryan: THAT'S EVEN A SHADOW
SHADOW THERE, ISN'T IT?
GOOD SHOT.
HE LOOKED VERY FIT IN THAT SHOP.
>> Kelly: MY SHADOWS ARE VERY
MUSCULAR.
MY SHADOWS HAVE A LOT OF CURVES.
>> Ryan: DIDN'T CAPTURE YOU
BUT CAPTURED YOUR SHADOW.
>> Kelly: I CAPTURED MY OWN
SHADOW.
MARK TOOK A PICTURE OF PLANTS.
I ACCIDENTALLY DRIFTED BY.
>> Ryan: IT WAS GREAT.
I WAS GONE A LONG TIME AS WELL,
DID GO OVERSEAS WERE LITTLE
CONVENTION FOR THE RADIO SHOW,
THEN I WENT BACK TO L.A. FOR A
DAY.
THEN I WENT BACK TO GREECE TO
GET SOME SUN AFTERWARDS.
IT IS JUST BEAUTIFUL, THE PEOPLE
ARE GREAT, FOOD IS GREAT BUT
DURING ALL OF THIS BECAUSE I
HAVE THIS NICE NOW, EVERY FIRST
IS A BIG DEAL IN THE FAMILY SO
MY SISTER WAS SO NERVOUS ABOUT
TRAVELING WITH BABY FLORA FOR
THE FIRST TIME ON THE PLANE.
SO HERE THEY ARE, JUST WANT TO
SHOW YOU, JIMMY AND MEREDITH AND
FLORA ON THEIR FIRST FLIGHT.
>> Kelly: ADORABLE.
>> Ryan: SHE WAS SO CONCERNED
ABOUT HOW SHE WAS GOING TO DO,
WAS SHE GOING TO BE A MESS,
SCREAMING AND CRYING.
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE SHE ENJOYED
HERSELF.
>> Kelly: I CANNOT BELIEVE SHE
IS MY SIZE.
>> Ryan: SHE IS OUR SIZE.
>> Kelly: THAT IS THE OUTFIT I
WORE ON THE SHOW LAST WEEK.
>> Ryan: ONE OF THE THINGS I
DISCOVERED BECAUSE I LOVE TO EAT
AND SNACK ESPECIALLY WHILE ON
VACATION, TOOK THE CLOCKS OUT OF
MY ROOM SO I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
TIME IT WAS IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
NIGHT OR WHAT TIME IT WAS IN THE
MORNING SO I SLEPT UNTIL I WOKE
UP.
THE GREATEST THING EVER.
>> Kelly: YOU SLEPT UNTIL I
TEXTED YOU.
>> Ryan: YOU AND MARK HAVE
PB&J'S ALL THE TIME.
I HAD EVERY DAY ON VACATION OF
PBJ BE.
PEANUT BUTTER JELLY AND BACON.
YOU'RE WELCOME AS WELL, AMERICA
AND CANADA.
I LEAVE YOU WITH THIS TREE
TODAY.
MAKE YOURSELF A PB B.
YOU ARE SHAKING.
ARE YOU EXCITED?
THIS IS WHAT YOU GUYS SHOULD BE
MAKING BECAUSE MARK LOVES TO EAT
THESE IN BED, RIGHT?
>> Kelly: WE WERE IN CORSICA
FIRST AND THEN WE WENT TO ITALY
AND DID NOT HAVE ACCESS.
COULD HAVE CONJURED UP ACCESS TO
PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY BUT WE
LIKE TO EAT LOCAL, WOULD LIKE TO
EAT WHAT LOCAL PEOPLE EAT SO WE
WERE HAVING LOTS OF FRESH FOOD.
FRESH FISH, WE HAD PASTA EVERY
DAY AND IT WAS HOMEMADE AND WE
WENT TO A FARM WHERE THEY MAKE
AND WE DID THE WHOLE THING.
AND HE OF COURSE BECAUSE HE WAS
WITHOUT PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY
FORM TWO WEEKS LOST 5 POUNDS.
>> Ryan: BECAUSE HE NEEDED TO.
>> Kelly: HE LOST 5 POUNDS.
JUST SKIPPING PEANUT BUTTER AND
JELLY.
>> Ryan: NO KIDDING, I KNOW.
IT STARTS THE BACON IN THERE.
SLIDE IT RIGHT IN.
LOTS OF NEWS OVER THE LAST
COUPLE OF DAYS, THESE TWO
EARTHQUAKES IN
SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA, REAL
SERIOUS.
TO BACK-TO-BACK BASICALLY IN THE
LAST 17.1 WHICH IS AN EIGHT
TIMES STRONGER THAN THE FIRST
ONE.
>> Kelly: THAT'S SO
INTERESTING BECAUSE I WAS
WATCHING THAT ON CNN EXPLAINING
IT, SO FIRST ONE WAS 6.4 AND
THEN THE 7.1.
IT'S NOT THAT MUCH, DOESN'T IT
SEEM LIKE BIG OF A SHIFT AND
APPARENTLY IT'S EXPONENTIAL.
>> Ryan: EVERY DECIMAL IS THAT
FULL AMOUNT OF TIMES.
SO IT IS SIGNIFICANT.
I HAVE BEEN IN THEM BEFORE.
I HAVE NOT MOVED TO L.A. YET.
SO THREES AND FOURS AND SO SCARE
YOU.
>> Kelly: MY SON WAS OUT IN
CALIFORNIA, MY OLDEST SON AND HE
WAS IN L.A. PROPER HE SAID THEY
COULD FEEL EARTHQUAKES.
THEY FELT THAT.
>> Ryan: YOU FEEL ONE WHEN YOU
STOP SLEEPING NAKED.
YOU JUST NEVER KNOW WHEN YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO RUN INTO THE
DOORJAMB.
SHE WAS BY THE SIDE OF THE BED.
>> Kelly: IT DEPENDS ON WHO'S
HOUSE HERE IN.
>> Ryan: GENERALLY I LIKE TO
SLEEP ON MY OWN.
>> Kelly: DON'T SLEEP NAKED IN
MY HOUSE BECAUSE THE KIDS WILL
WALK IN AT ANY SECOND.
DON'T YOU EVER PUT CLOTHES ON?
AND I'M LIKE DON'T YOU KNOCK?
ANYWAY, SO IT SO INTERESTING,
THEY'RE SO MUCH TO TALK ABOUT IN
SPORTS.
THE WOMEN'S SOCCER TEAM.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Ryan: INCREDIBLE, SO GREAT.
>> Kelly: I, WHO DON'T WATCH
WATCH AND I SAID I CANNOT
BELIEVE I'VE BEEN MISSING THE
SPORT FOR SO MANY YEARS.
>> Ryan: IT'S INCREDIBLE,
RIGHT?
>> Kelly: MIKE HUSBAND AND
KIDS ALWAYS WATCH SOCCER AND
I'VE DRIFTED IN AND OUT.
THEY ARE SO GOOD.
AND I WAS SO JUST UNABASHEDLY
HAPPY FOR THEM.
>> Ryan: THE GOING TO BE
CELEBRATED WEDNESDAY, A BIG
PARADE IN THE CITY.
DOWNTOWN.
AND THEN ALEX MORGAN IS
NOMINATED FOR BEST FEMALE
ATHLETE AT THE SO
CONGRATULATIONS TO THAT TEAM.
DID YOU WATCH ANY OF THE TENNIS?
DID YOU SEE COCO?
>> Kelly: I DON'T FOLLOW
TENNIS BUT MARK SAYING THERE'S
THIS YOUNG GIRL NAMED COCO, IS A
GOLF WHO WAS 15 YEARS OLD AND IS
REALLY ON THIS WINNING STREAK AT
WIMBLEDON.
SO I HAVE A 16-YEAR-OLD SON AND
MY DAUGHTER WHO JUST TURNED 18.
YOU PICTURE THEM AT 15, ANY
15-YEAR-OLDS HERE?
HI, HIGH BACK THERE.
SO 15, MADE A RUN DOWN.
WHAT ARE YOU INTO?
>> Ryan: BACKSTREET BOYS?
THAT'S SO FUNNY, WE WERE TOO AS
TEENAGERS.
>> Kelly: SOMEBODY DOWN HERE
WAS YELLING.
WHAT ARE YOU INTO?
DANCE.
ARE YOU A COMPETITIVE DANCER?
>> NO.
>> Kelly: DON'T CLIMB UP NOW.
>> MUSICAL THEATER, ACTING, AND
SINGING.
>> Kelly: I WANT YOU TO
PICTURE THAT YOU'RE AT THE
OSCARS AND YOU ARE ON STAGE.
AND THIS IS FOR ALL THE MARBLES.
WE WERE ABOUT TO WIN THE
ACADEMY AWARD AND YOU ARE 15 AND
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
ARE YOU FREAKING OUT?
>> YES.
>> Kelly: THIS GIRL HAS NO
FREAK OUT, APPARENTLY.
>> Ryan: SHE IS SO POISED,
IT'S AMAZING TO SEE A
15-YEAR-OLD, THAT KIND OF POISE
AND THE TALENT AND THE SKILL.
BUT I DON'T HAVE KIDS BUT I WAS
THINKING ABOUT HOW DISCIPLINED
ONE MUST BE.
>> Kelly: HANG UP YOUR TRAVEL
ON A HOOK SO IT DOESN'T GET
MAILED TO YOU.
YOU CAN USE A TOWEL MORE THAN
ONCE.
RIGHT?
>> Ryan: JUST BECAUSE MY MOM
USED TO SAY THAT, I NOW LEAVE
THEM ON THE FLOOR JUST TO SPITE.
BUT I CAN'T REMEMBER IN YEARS
PAST, WATCHING SOME OF THE
WIMBLEDON AND THEY SPLIT SCREEN
ACTION.
THEY ASSUME THAT WE HAVE A LOT
OF CAPACITY AS VIEWERS BECAUSE
WATCHING TWO MATCHES AT THE SAME
TIME.
>> Kelly: YOU MEAN THEY PLAY
TWO MATCHES?
I THOUGHT THEY SPLIT SCREEN SO
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS THE
WHOLE TIME.
>> Ryan: THEY SPLIT SCREEN TWO
ACTION SHOTS.
THEY ARE VERY AMBITIOUS AND THEY
THINK I HAVE A LOT OF CAPACITY
TO UNDERSTAND WHAT'S GOING ON
YOU CAN WATCH TWO MATCHES AT
ONCE.
I HAD NOT SEEN THAT BEFORE.
THIS WAS LIVE-ACTION, TWO
DIFFERENT COURTS, REALLY
CHALLENGING.
I WAS EXHAUSTED.
AFTER WATCHING.
>> Kelly: IT SOUNDS
EXHAUSTING.
AND THE WHOLE SCORING SYSTEM IS
ALWAYS HARD AND CHALLENGING FOR
ME.
BECAUSE IT GOES BY 15.
>> Ryan: UNTIL YOU GET TO 40.
>> Kelly: I DON'T KNOW WHAT
COMES NEXT.
>> Ryan: TODAY, WE LOVE THE
SHOW.
TODAY ON THE SHOW, KUMAIL
NANJIANI IS WITH US.
HE'S GOT A GREAT NEW MOVIE, VERY
FUNNY, "STUBER" ."
>> Kelly: AND
BERNADETTE PETERS IS BACK, SHE'S
BROUGHT SOME PUPS WHO ARE UP FOR
ADOPTION.
>> Ryan: THERE'S A LAB MIX.
I'M NOT LOOKING, BUT THERE IS A
LAB MIX AND I'M A SUCKER FOR A
LAB.
WE ARE GOING TO SEE IF WE KNOW
THE FACTS ABOUT OUR DOGS WHEN WE
PLAY A GAME OF TRUTH OR TAIL.
I GOT IT.
BUT NOW, IT'S TIME FOR "STUMP
THE HOSTS TRAVEL TRIVIA!"
LET'S DO IT.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Ryan: CHRISTINE MILLS FROM
BOHEMIA LONG ISLAND.
>> Kelly: BOHEMIA, THAT SOUNDS
LIKE WHERE I WANT TO LIVE.
>> IT'S VERY EXOTIC.
>> Ryan: YOUR VERY BOHEMIAN.
TODAY, BOTH OUR STUDIO AUDIENCE
AND YOU WENT HOME CAN WEIGH IN
ON WHICH STATEMENT YOU THINK IS
TRUE.
JUST FOR VOTING, YOU CAN HAVE A
CHANCE TO WIN YOUR OWN KELLY AND
RYAN MUG.
THERE SHE IS.
>> Kelly: JUST LOOK AT ITS
MAJESTY.
>> Ryan: SO WE'VE GOT WHO
WATCHES US.
GOOD MORNING, HOW ARE YOU?
>> Caller: I'M GOOD, HOW ARE
Y'ALL?
>> Ryan: WHAT ARE YOU UP TO
THIS MORNING?
COLOR MATCH IS FIXING TO GO
RUNNING WITH MY DAUGHTER AND YOU
CALLED.
SO GOING TO TAKE THE DAY OFF.
>> Kelly: YOU WERE GOING TO GO
RUNNING?
>> Caller: I WAS GOING TO GO
RUNNING BUT NOW I DON'T HAVE TO.
>> Kelly: I JUST WANT YOU TO
KNOW, THIS PHONE CALL IS GOING
TO TAKE ABOUT 2 MINUTES.
>> Ryan: YOU SHOULDN'T BLOW
OFF YOUR RUN FOR THIS.
I'LL SPEED IT UP RIGHT NOW SO
YOU CAN GET TO IT.
TWO STATEMENTS, GOING TO TRY TO
GUESS WHICH ONE IS TRUE.
IF YOU STUMP US, YOU WIN THE MU
MUG.
FIRST OF HER STATEMENTS, WHEN I
WAS YOUNGER, I COULD STICK MY
ENTIRE FIST IN MY MOUTH.
>> Kelly: I KNEW SOMEONE WHO
COULD DO THAT.
>> Ryan: YOU CAN CALL ME BY MY
NAME.
WHEN I CAN YOU DO THAT TOO?
>> Ryan: I'VE NEVER TRIED IT.
OR I MADE IT TO THE SEMIFINALS
OF THE DALLAS COWBOYS
CHEERLEADERS TRYOUTS.
>> Kelly: I SO WANT TO BELIEVE
THAT.
SO I'M LOOKING AT YOU AND I'M
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT.
I WISHED HER HAND WAS IN THIS
PHOTO SO I COULD SEE YOUR MOUTH
TO FIST RATIO.
IT >> Ryan: SO SHE COULD SCALE
IT.
>> Kelly: WHAT WAS THE KEY TO
MAKING IT TO THE SEMIFINALS IN
THE DALLAS COWBOYS CHEERLEADER
TRYOUTS?
>> Caller: YOU HAD TO HAVE
YOUR OWN DANCE AND YOU HAD TO DO
IT FOR 90 SECONDS AND MY AUNT
WAS A DANCER.
SO SHE TAUGHT ME A DANCE AND
THEN YOU HAD TO GO AND PERFORM.
HE DID AS A GROUP AND EVERYBODY
JUST PLAYED MUSIC AND YOU KIND
OF DANCE AROUND.
SO I KNEW IT I WAS GOING TO DO
SO I DID THAT.
>> Ryan: SUSPECT.
HOW DID YOU DISCOVER YOUR FIST
TALENT?
>> Caller: I DON'T KNOW.
A BOY IN MY JUNIOR HIGH DID IT
TOO SO OUR PICTURES GOT PUT IN
THE YEARBOOK, BUT THEN I HAD TO
QUIT IN HIGH SCHOOL, THEY KIND
OF STARTED RIPPING THE SIDES OF
MY MOUTH.
>> Kelly: THIS IS TAKING A
DARK TURN.
>> Ryan: WHAT YOU GUYS THINK?
HERE'S WHAT'S INTERESTING.
>> Kelly: USED TO WATCH THAT
SHOW ABOUT THE DALLAS COWBOYS
CHEERLEADER TRYOUTS, THEY HAD A
SHOW.
Y'ALL REMEMBER THAT SHOW?
AND I REMEMBER THEM HAVING A
VERY CHOREOGRAPHED ROUTINE THAT
THEY HAD TO MEMORIZE IN ONE
SECOND.
I DON'T REMEMBER.
>> Caller: FREE STYLING IS THE
VERY BEGINNING ONE.
THAT'S THE PRELIMS AND THEN THE
IS WHEN THEY GET YOU AT THE END.
PERFORM IN FRONT OF THEM.
>> Kelly: THAT'S NOT WHAT YOU
SAID WHEN I QUESTIONED YOU WITH
MY INTENSIVE QUESTIONING.
>> Ryan: I WAS RIGHT HERE.
I WAS READY.
WHAT ARE WE GOING WITH?
>> Kelly: I DON'T KNOW, I'M
GOING TO SAY FIST AND MOUTH
BECAUSE I AM LOOKING AT HER
GREAT BEAUTIFUL WIDE SMILE.
WHICH ALSO COULD WORK TO THE
CHEERLEADING THING BUT I THINK
IT'S FIST AND MOUTH.
>> Ryan: IS IT FIST IN THE
MOUTH?
>> Caller: THAT'S TRUE.
>> Ryan: GOT IT.
GO WITH THE GOT ALWAYS.
HAVEN'T LOST IT.
>> Kelly: I'VE STILL GOT IT.
>> Ryan: EVEN THOUGH YOU
DIDN'T WIN THE MUG, GOING TO
SPIN THE WHEEL AND SEE WHAT
YOU'RE PLAYING FOR.
WHAT DO WE HAVE?
>> Kelly: THIS IS A GREAT
PRIZE.
JW MARRIOTT CANCUN SPINE RESORT
IN CANCUN MEXICO.
SEVEN DAYS, SIX NIGHTS IN A
OCEANVIEW ROOM.
IT INCLUDES $1400 FOOD AND
BEVERAGE CREDIT, A SPA TREATMENT
PER PERSON, A PRIZE VALUED AT
$7400, YOU HAVE 20 SECONDS AND
ONLY ONE GUESS, GOOD LUCK.
>> Ryan: ON FRIDAY SHOW, WE
TALKED WITH RICKY GERVAIS US.
IN WHAT TOWN OUTSIDE LONDON DID
HE SAY HE LIVES?
>> Caller: IT WAS HEMPSTEAD.
>> Kelly: YES!
>> Announcer: CONGRATULATIONS!
YOU AND A GUEST WILL ENJOY SEVEN
DAYS AND SIX NIGHTS OF LOUNGING
IT OUT MOST LUXURY AT THE JW
MARRIOTT CANCUN RESORT AND SPA.
HOSTING AN EXTENSIVE SELECTION
OF UPSCALE ACCOMMODATIONS,
GUESTS WILL ENJOY ENDLESS
BEACHES, TURQUOISE WATERS,
EXPANSIVE POOLS, A VARIETY OF
ON-SITE RESTAURANTS WITH FRESH
AND AUTHENTIC TASTES, A MAYAN
INSPIRED SPOT, AND MUCH MORE.
IF YOUR PRIZE IS VALUED AT
APPROXIMATELY $7,400.
>> Ryan: THAT LOOKS GREAT.
>> Caller: THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I HAVE KIND OF A SAD STORY.
WE CAME TO NEW YORK, PLANNED OUR
TRIP AROUND Y'ALL LAST YEAR
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T GET TICKETS
UNTIL A FEW MONTHS AHEAD OF
TIME, THEY DON'T PUT IT ON
THERE.
SO WHEN WE WERE THERE RIGHT WHEN
YOU WERE ALL GONE.
>> Kelly: FOR OUR VACATION.
NOW YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE A TRIP.
>> Ryan: TICKETS ARE NOT HARD
TO GET.
THEY ARE FREE.
>> Caller: THANK YOU BUT
>> Kelly: BUT SHE IS ON THE
PHONE WITH US, WE CAN PUT IT ON
HOLD AND GIVE HER TICKETS FOR
WHEN SHE COMES BACK.
>> Ryan: WE ARE GOING TO WORK
THIS OUT AND PUT YOU ON YOUR
RUN, OKAY?
>> Kelly: ONE MORE THING, YOU
HAVE TO HELP US MAKE THAT THEY
HAVE A LUCKY MEMBER OF OUR
STUDIO AUDIENCE WHOSE GOING TO
RECEIVE A $500 GIFT CERTIFICATE
FROM BARNES & NOBLE SO PLEASE
PICK A NUMBER BETWEEN 1 AN END
212.
>> Caller: 28.
>> Ryan: 28.
RIGHT THERE.
CONGRATULATIONS, GOOD JOB,
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> Announcer: STILL AHEAD ON
"LIVE," WE WILL TEST OUR DOG
KNOWLEDGE WITH
BERNADETTE PETERS.
WE WILL OPEN THE INBOX FOR YOUR
COMMENTS AND QUESTIONS.
I'M COMING UP NEXT, KUMAIL
NANJIANI.
>> Ryan: AND WASH HER HANDS
FIRST.
>> Kelly: HE'S AN
OSCAR-NOMINATED SCREENWRITER,
STAND-UP COMEDIAN WHO NOW STARS
AND THEY KNEW ACTION COMEDY WITH
DAVE BAUTISTA, PLEASE WELCOME
KUMAIL NANJIANI.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Kumail: HI!
>> Kelly: GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> Ryan: WELCOME BACK.
>> Kumail: THANK YOU.
WHY IS IT SO SMOKY IN HERE?
WHAT IS GOING ON?
>> Kelly: APPARENTLY THEY ARE
SPECIAL-EFFECTS FOR OUR TRIVIA
GAME.
>> Kumail: YOU'RE GOING TO
INJURE A LOT OF PEOPLE WITH THIS
FIST AND MOUTH CHECK.
CAN I DO THAT?
NO.
I'M NOT GOINGTION
RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS WHEN THE ALIENS SHOULD
SHOW UP AND JUST TAKE OVER.
>> Ryan: IT'S GOOD TIMING.
>> Kumail: DO YOU BELIEVE?
>> Ryan: I DON'T BELIEVE
THAT'S A FLYING SAUCER.
IT'S AN UNIDENTIFIED FLYING
OBJECT.
>> Kelly: YOU THINK I SAW
SERENITY CUP, NO.
>> Ryan: THE MILITARY SAYS
THAT THEY DON'T KNOW, BUT THEY
HAVE TO KNOW.
>> Kelly: I LIKE THAT YOUR AIR
QUOTING EVERYTHING.
I DON'T KNOW, BUT THEY HAVE TO
KNOW.
>> Ryan: DID YOU RECENTLY
THROW THE FIRST PITCH AT A
BASEBALL GAME?
>> Kumail: I THREW THE FIRST
PITCH, YEAH.
>> Ryan: DID IT GO OVER THE
PLATE?
>> Kumail: IT WENT OVER THE
PLATE.
>> Kelly: AND WE SHOW THAT
PICTURE ONE MORE TIME?
THAT LOOKS LIKE A STAGED PHOTO,
LIKE THEY SUPERIMPOSED YOUR HEAD
ONTO AN ACTION SHOT.
>> Kumail: I'M IN FRONT OF A
GREEN SCREEN, THROUGHOUT THE
FIRST PITCH.
>> Kelly: THAT'S A GREAT SHOT.
>> Kumail: THAT PHOTOGRAPHER
WAS AMAZING.
EVERY PICTURE, I LOOKED LIKE
ROBERT REDFORD OR SOMETHING.
HOW DID IT GO FOR YOU?
TO MECCA DIDN'T GO OVER THE
PLATE.
>> Kelly: HOW ABOUT FOR YOU?
>> Kumail: IT WENT OVER THE
PLATE.
>> Ryan: GOOD FOR YOU.
>> Kelly: THANK YOU, DADDY.
>> Ryan: WE ARE GOING TO TALK
ABOUT WHAT IT'S LIKE ON ABC7 AN
NEWS RIGHT AFTER THIS.
>> JESSOB: WE ARE FOLLOWING
BREAKING NEWS RIGHT NOW, AN
IMMENSE AMOUNT OF RAIN HITTING
DMV RIGHT NOW.
LET'S GET OUT TO JOHN GONZALEZ
IN ARLINGTON.
INCREDIBLE IMAGES, THAT RED CAR
SUBMERGED.
PERSONAL BELONGINGS OUT OF THE
DOORS INTO THE WATER, GOOD
MORNING.
>> JOHN: JESSOB, GOOD MORNING.
WE STARTED IN BOYDS, MARYLAND ON
THE WOMEN'S WORLD CUP.
STORM CAME THROUGH THERE FIRST
AND CONTINUED DOWN I-270
CORRIDOR.
NOW THROUGH ARLINGTON AND D.C.
CITY.
THIS IS KENA BECK IN ARLINGTON.
THERE WAS A CALL FOR A WOMAN ON
TOP OF THE VEHICLE.
WE ARE HOPING SHE GOT HELP.
TOO MUCH RAIN IN A SHORT AMOUNT
OF TIME.
THAT CAR IS REVERSING.
TURN AROUND DON'T DROWNED, YOU
HEAR IT ALL THE TIME.
PERFECT EXAMPLE OF WHAT WE TALK
ABOUT WHEN WE SAY THAT ON THE
AIR.
SMALL VEHICLE.
ANOTHER SEE DAN TO THE RIGHT OF
US TRYING TO GET THROUGH THAT
STANDING WATER NEXT TO WEST OVER
PARK.
THEY ARE REVERSING.
THEY HAVE TO DO THAT CAREFULLY.
BACK TO THIS VEHICLE.
RED HONDA.
YOU SEE THE BACK.
HOPING THAT THE NEWS IS GOOD,
THIS WOMAN ABLE TO GET OUT
WITHOUT INJURIES.
WE DON'T SEE PARAMEDICS OR FIRST
RESPONDERS.
THOR UP THE HILL A BIT.
JUST A SCARY SITUATION, STEVE.
TOO MUCH RAIN.
MANHOLE COMPLETELY OVERWHELMED.
MANHOLE SEWER SYSTEM CAN'T TAKE
THIS RAIN.
>> STEVE: THIS IS CONTACTUALLY
WHAT FLASH FLOOD IS.
IF YOU LOOK AT THE TOPOGRAPHY,
IT IS IN A LOW LYING AREA.
ALL THIS WATER POOLING IN THIS
ONE LOCATION.
THIS IS WHAT FLASH FLOODING IS
ALL ABOUT.
DOESN'T TAKE LONG, HAPPENS IN A
FLASH.
COULD HAPPEN IN A MINUTE, TWO
MINUTES.
THIS IS WHY YOU DON'T GO ACROSS
THE ROADS.
YOU MIGHT SAY TO YOURSELF OR
THINK I HAVE TRAVELED THIS ROUTE
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
LOOKS LIKE TWO OR THREE INCHES.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT, SIX INCH,
TEN INCHES, TWO FEET OF WATER.
YOUR CAR IS SHOT AND NOT
WORKING.
JOHNNY G., WE'LL LET HIM TALK TO
THAT PERSON.
THIS IS UPPER NORTHWEST D.C.
HEAVY RAIN CANTS TO FALL.
THIS IS GOING ON 20-25 MINUTES.
BECAUSE OF THE TIMING OF THIS
STORM, HEAVY RAIN MAKER A LOT OF
FOLKS HAVE PUT OFF LEAVING TO GO
TO NORTH THANK GOODNESS STILL ON
VACATION.
IN TERMS OF MOVEMENT BOTH
DIRECTIONS OVER TO GEORGETOWN.
FLASH FLOOD CONTINUES ALL AREAS
CLOSE TO CAPITAL BELTWAY WHETHER
YOU ARE IN SILVER SPRING OR
WHEATON OR ANACOSTIA, OXON HILL,
CAPITOL HILL ALL THIS SLOWLY TO
THE SOUTH.
ALEXANDRIA ANOTHER HALF HOUR TO
45 MINUTES, YOU ARE GOING TO
START TO DRY OUT.
IF YOU ARE GOING GOING TO BE
>> ADRIANNA: MAJOR WATER LEAK
RIGHT NOW.
HERE IS A VIDEO RIGHT NOW OF
ARLINGTON.
VISIBILITY EXTREMELY POOR.
FAA TWEETED OUT, SEVERAL MAJOR
AIRPORT EFFECTED BY THIS
WEATHER, MIAMI, FORT LAUDERDALE
ALL THE WAY UP NORTH TO
LAGUARDIA.
THOSE AIRPORTS COULD EXPERIENCE
DELAYS, REAGAN AND DULLES.
MONTGOMERY COUNTY DEALING WITH A
LOT OF CREEKS AND STREAMS
OVERFLOWING WITH WATER.
PEOPLE TRYING TO MAKE THEIR WAY,
HEAVY AND SWIFT.
PEOPLE TRYING TO RUN THROUGH IT
AND AGAIN TO DRY SPACE.
>> DOESN'T SEEK LIKE, VERONICA
HASN'T MENTIONED THUNDERSTORMS
OR LIGHTNING OR HIGH WINDS.
SIMPLY A LOT OF WATER.
OUR JOHN GONZALEZ OUT THERE
LIVE.
LOOKS LIKE A WATER RESCUE BEHIND
YOU GOING ON.
>> FIRST RESPONDERS HERE, YOU
CAN SEE WHAT WAS LEFT BEHIND,
NEIGHBORS HELPING THE DRIVER OF
THE VEHICLE GETTING HER
BELONGINGS.
THIS IS THE YOUNG LADY, DRIVER
WITH THE BING JACKET.
CAR WAS PARKED SHE CAME OUT TO
DRY TO MOVE IT.
THAT IS THE SITUATION HERE ON
KENA BECK STREET AND 11TH.
TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF STANDING
WATER, FLASH FLOODING AT ITS
BEST.
STAIRWELL COMPLETELY FLOODED.
TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF FLOODING
AND LIGHTNING.
JOHN IF YOU PAN OVER TO THE BALL
FIELD.
OUT FIELD OF THE BASEBALL FIELD
COMPLETELY UNDER WATER.
YOU GET THE WATER, COMES IN,
FLASH FLOODING.
VERY, VERY DANGEROUS.
WE SAW A MAN GOING DOWN THE ROAD
AND QUICKLY REALIZED.
SAYS HE HAD AN APPOINTMENT.
YOU CAN SEE THE VEHICLES ARE
TURNING AROUND AS THEY SEE THE
STANDING WATER AT 11 KEN BECK IN
ARLINGTON.
WE WERE LIVE DOING A STORY.
HERE YOU HAVE IT ARLINGTON AND
D.C.
GOOD NEWS IS THE DRIVER IS OKAY.
>> ADRIANNA: JOHNNY.
YOU MENTIONED YOU HAVE BEEN
CAUGHT IN THE RAIN EVER SINCE
THIS MORNING.
SUDDENLY THE RAIN POURED DOWN ON
YOU.
EXPLAIN WHAT YOU HAVE SEEN FROM
THAT MOMENT THEN DOWN TO
ARLINGTON AND WHERE YOU ARE NOW.
HOW DID YOU SEE THAT WEATHER
PROGRESS CHANGE?
>> WE HAD A LIVE REPORT COMING
UP AT 7:00.
WE SAW THOSE CLOUDS COMING.
WITHIN MINUTES, RAIN CAME DOWN,
LIGHTSENING.
INTERESTING TO WATCH.
AS WE WERE COMING DOWN 270 ON
THE BELTWAY, WE COULD SEE THE
STORM FOLLOWING US.
THIS IS WHAT IT IS CREATING.
SAME SITUATION WE WERE
WITNESSING UP NORTH IN UPPER
MONTGOMERY COUNTY.
GAITHERSBURG, GERMANTOWN.
NUMBER OF ROAD CLOSURES, FLASH
FLOODING.
NOW HIT D.C. AND ARLINGTON.
CARS PARKED NOW IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE ROAD.
POWER IS JUST ENORMOUS.
GENTLEMAN PULLED UP IN A PICK UP
TRUCK.
LOOKS LIKE HE IS GOING TO HELP
THIS YOUNG LADY GET THIS CAR OUT
OF HERE.
PEOPLE INSIDE, MAYBE CHILDREN.
LITTLE STUFFED ANIMALS THAT
FLOATED AWAY.
GOOD NEWS, BEEN ABLE TO TALK TO
THE DRIVER.
STARTLING MORNING FOR HER.
SHE SAYS AGAIN SHE SAW THE
STANDING WATER, SHE SAW THE ROAD
QUICKLY SUBMERGED AND TRIED TO
MOVE HER CAR, TOO LATE.
SHE DID NOT HAVE ENOUGH TIME.
>> MELANIE: JOHN, WE WERE
WATCHING THE SITUATION UNFOLD
WITH THE CAR.
IT IS DIFFICULT FOR US TO ASSESS
HOW HEAVILY THE RAIN IS COMING
DOWN LOOKING AT THE TV SCREEN.
MODERATE RAIN FALL?
TAPERING OFF ANY?
>> JOHN: I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
TAPERING DOWN, IT IS STILL
COMING DOWN AT A GOOD CLIP.
NOT TORRENTIAL.
INTO THE BELTWAY, AGAIN A
TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF RAIN YOU
CAN PROBABLY SEE IT ON TOP OF
THE STANDING WATER.
THAT GIVES YOU AN IDEA OF HOW
MUCH RAIN WE ARE STILL GETTING.
WE ARE GOING TO TRY TO MOVE THE
CAR ON OUR OWN.
GOOD THING WE DID.
>> VERONICA: AMAZING SHOT,
JOHNNY.
OTHER RESCUES SIMILAR TO THAT.
IF WE CAN SPLIT THE SCREEN FOR
THE VIDEO BACK UP.
I WAS IN ELLICOTT CITY EARLIER
FOR BOTH FLASH FLOOD EVENTS.
THAT IS WHY IT IS CALLED FLASH
FLOODING IT CAN OCCUR IN A FLASH
WHERE YOU HAVE THAT MUCH WATER
THAN ACCUMULATES SO QUICKLY.
THAT IS THE REASON WE CALL IT
FLASH FLOODING.
WATER COMES UP IN A HURRY, HAS
NOWHERE TO GO ESPECIALLY IF YOU
ARE IN AN AREA TRAVELING THROUGH
AN AREA OR LIVE IN AN AREA WITH
A LOT OF THE OF CONCRETE.
GROUND CANNOT PICK UP THAT
WATER, CANNOT TAKE IN THAT
WATER.
HEAVY RAIN DURING THE AFTERNOON
WITH THESE SUMMER STORMS.
IT IS ON THE FAR LEFT HAND
PORTION OF YOUR SCREEN HARD TO
SEE AS HEAVY RAIN CONTINUES
THROUGH THE NATION'S CAPITOL.
THERE IS A LOOK AT THE CAPITOL
DOME.
WHAT TYPICALLY IS A WARNING FOR
US, BY THIS TIME WE CAN SEE
BETTER OVER THE LAST HOUR AND A
HALF TO TWO HOURS.
HERE IS A LOOK AT CLARKSBURG
ROAD, THIS IS I-270, SOME OF THE
HEAVIEST HAS ALREADY COME
THROUGH.
IF YOU ARE IN NORTHERN WESTERN
MONTGOMERY COUNTY SEEING CREEKS,
STREAMS ALSO CONTINUE TO COME UP
ACROSS THE AREA.
LOOK AT THE RADAR.
YOU HEARD JOHNNY GONZALEZ, THIS
IS WHERE HE WAS EARLIER.
HE TRAVELED WITH THAT LINE DOWN
TO THE SOUTH INTO THE METRO
AREA, SOUTH AND EAST READY TO
PULL INTO PORTIONS OF NORTHERN
CHARLES COUNTY.
LOOK AT DUNKIRK.
NEAR 301 AND SOUTH OF BOWIE.
IMPROVEMENT AROUND DAMASCUS,
ELLICOTT CITY.
1:00 P.M., CONTINUE TO HAVE
THREAT OF FLASH FLOODING.
LET'S GO BACK TO JOHN GONZALEZ
WHO HAS MORE ON THE FLASH
FLOODING.
COMPLETELY SUBMERGED WHEN WE
ARRIVED.
CAR WAS PARKED, KEN BECK STREET
AND 11TH.
YOU CAN'T GET CALLED.
YOU HAPPEN TO COME ACROSS THIS.
CLOSE TO HOME AND SAW THEM
LOCKED UP.
NOT BAD WEATHER, BAD
PREPARATION.
DECIDED TO CRUISE AROUND.
YOU CAN USE SOME SORT OF
INFERENCE TO KNOW HOW DEEP IT IS
UNLESS YOU HAVE A LARGER
VEHICLE, I WOULDN'T RECOMMEND
IT.
JOHN GONZALEZ THANKS FOR HELPING
THIS YOUNG LADY GET OUT OF THE
WATER.
JOHN, IF YOU PAN THE CAMERA.
YOU CAN SEE HER TRYING TOO
COLLECT HER PERSONAL BELONGINGS.
YOU CAN SEE WHAT I SAID EARLIER,
HAVE BEEN TALK ABOUT THE FLASH
FLOODING.
WATER RESOOEDZ IN 10 MINUTES.
YOU HAVE VEHICLES AT THE TOP
RECEDES BLACK SUV DOING THE
SMART THING.
JUST TAKES A MATTER OF SECONDS
TO GET YOURSELF IN A LOT OF
TROUBLE.
VERONICA, BACK TO YOU INSIDE.
>> VERONICA: THAT'S WHEN WE SAY
THE AREA IS UNDER A FLASH FLOOD
WATCH.
THAT IS WHEN YOU NEED TO PREPARE
AND STAY WITH STORM WATCH 7,
ALWAYS HAVE THAT WEATHER APP
RAIDY TO GO.
MAKE SURE THE NOTIFICATIONS ARE
RE
READY.
HOW MUCH LONGER UNTIL 2:00, 3:00
P.M.  I HAVE PUT ON A COUPLE OF
AMOUNTS HERE IN TERMS OF RAIN
FALL WHAT WE HAVE SEEN ADDISON
HEIGHTS, 2.4 INCHES OF RAIN.
NORTH OF MACLAINE, CLOSE TO FIVE
INCHES OF RAIN.
AGAIN, NOT IN A 24 HOUR PERIOD A
LOT OF TIMES.
THIS IN AN HOUR TO HOUR AND A
HALF.
VERY QUICKLY.
OUT OF THE STORM DRAINS CAN'T
TAKE THE WATER.
SITS ON THE ROAD AND INCREASES
QUICKLY IN A FOOT OF ROAD CAN
CARRY YOUR CAR AWAY EASILY.
THAT MUCH WATER, DON'T EVER
ATTEMPT TO DRIVE ACROSS A
FLOODED ROAD.
LOOK AT WESTERN PORTIONS OF
MONTGOMERY COUNTY, ROCKVILLE,
WEST OF 270, 3.4 INCHES OF RAIN.
THIS LOOP OVER THE LAST THREE
HOURS.
DOING BETTER, JOHNNY GONZALEZ
MENTION HOW THINGS ARE
IMPROVING.
IT WILL TAKE TIME FOR CREEKS,
RIVERS, STREAMS.
KIDS OUT OF SCHOOL TODAY.
MAKE SURE THEY ARE NOT IN THE
BACKYARD HEAVIEST RAIN WITH
LIGHTNING COMING PRINCE GEORGE'S
COUNTY AROUND 301 CROSSING OVER
MAKING ITS WAY VERY SLOWLY AND
SOUTHEAST.
MAKES ITS WAY SOUTH FROM BOWIE
AND SOUTH OF ANNAPOLIS.
HEAVY RAIN, ALEXANDRIA SOUTH TO
MOUNT VERNON DOWN ROUTE ONE.
SOUTH OF SILVER HILL AND DOWN TO
CLINTON AND FRANCONIA.
LIVE IN THESE AREAS, STAY PUT.
TREAT IT JUST AS YOU WOULD A
SEVERE THUNDERSTORM WARNING.
THIS IS A LIFE AND DEATH
SITUATION.
HOWARD COUNTY, 11:45.
AROUND ELLICOTT CITY OR KATEN
VILS.
THIS
>>> please stand by
WE SEEN AND HOW MUCH TIME?
>> THERE HAVE BEEN JACKPOT ZONES
IN ARLINGTON OVER TO MACLAINE,
OVER TO POTOMAC, THEN YOU HEAD
OVER INTO EASTERN MONTGOM