I WAS REALLY FORTUNATE.
I MOVED TO LA WITH A JOB
ALREADY.
AND THAT'S SO RARE AND,, MAN, I
WAS VERY, VERY LUCKY.
>> WHAT WAS YOUR REACTION WHEN
SOMEONE CALLS YOU AND SAYS I AM
THE CREATIVE DIRECTOR FOR JANET
JACKSON.
>> LET PLEA ACT IT OUT FOR YOU.
>> OKAY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> ♪♪
♪
♪ WHAT'S MY NAME ♪
♪ THAT'S IT, WATCH IT SAY IT ♪
>> YOU ARE GOING TO SHOW ME SOME
MOVES I BELIEVE, RIGHT?
>> I AM GOING TEACH YOU SOME
MOVES.
>> SCARED.
>> READY.
RIGHT FOOT AND DOWN.
BOOM.
THEN SWITCH IT.
SWITCH IT AGAIN.
SWITCH THE LEGS, LIFT THE BODY.
GOOD.
THERE YOU GO.
SWITCH THE BODY, SWITCH THE
LEGS.
NICE.
NOW LOOK TO THE RIGHT AND LOOK
BACK.
AND SNAP.
>> SO --
>> ALMOST.
START SAME.
>> SAME.
>> AND SAME.
>> UH-HUH.
>> NOW YOU SWITCH IT AGAIN.
SAME.
>> OKAY.
>> NOW BRING IT UP.
AND SWITCH THE FEET.
LEAVE THE HANDS.
>> OH, YOU LEAVE THE HANDS.
>> NOW SWITCH THE FEET AND THE
HANDS, GOOD.
NOW LOOK.
>> RIGHT.
>> COME BACK.
>> LEFT.
>> AND SNAP.
YEAH.
>> LET'S DO IT AGAIN, FIVE, SIX,
READY GO.
BOOM, SWIM, SWITCH, BRING IT UP.
SWITCH IT.
LOOK.
LOOK BACK.
>> DID I GET IT?
HOW AM I DOING?
>> YOU TOTALLY PLAYED YOURSELF
DOWN.
>> DESCENDANTS 3?
♪ I CALL THE SHOTS YOU KNOW WHY
AM ♪
♪ STAND UP TO ME YOU DON'T STAND
A CHANCE ♪
♪ WE ARE NEXT ♪
♪ NOW I AM THE BEST ♪
♪ AND THIS WILL BE YOUR LAST
REGRET ♪
♪ WHAT'S MY NAME ♪
>>> COMING UP WE ARE GOING TO
GET IN TO THE ISLAND SPIRIT WITH
THE CHOREOGRAPHER FROM "MOANA",
TIANA LIUFAU.
♪ MADE IN HOLLYWOOD ♪
♪
>>> CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED
BY.
SMOKE MADE IN HOLLYWOOD ♪
♪
♪ MADE IN HOLLYWOOD ♪
>>> WE ARE BACK WITH THE
CHOREOGRAPHER FROM "MOANA",
TIANA LIUFAU.
>> CHOREOGRAPHERS WORK WITH THE
DIRECTOR IN ORDER TO CREATE
DANCE ROUTINES THAT HELP TELL
THE STORY OF THE MOVIE.
TIANA LIUFAU BEGAN DANCING AS
SOON AS SHE WAS ABLE TO WALK.
MS. LIUFAU CURRENTLY LEADS A
TAHITIAN MUSIC AND DANCE COMPANY
AND HAS BROUGHT TAHITIAN
CHOREOGRAPHER TO THE TELEVISION
SHOW "SO YOU THINK YOU CAN
DANCE."
>> DO YOU KNOW WHO MAUI IS?
ONLY THE GREATEST DEMIGOD IN ALL
THE PACIFIC ISLANDS.
WITH HIS MAGICAL FISH HOOK HE
SLOWS DOWN THE SUN.
PULLED ISLANDS OUT OF THE SEA.
BATTLED MONSTERS.
AND I SHOULD KNOW, BECAUSE I AM
MAUI.
♪♪
>> HEY.
LET ME DO THIS, PLEASE.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO WE ARE HERE
WITH TIANA LIUFAU, WHO IS THE
CHOREOGRAPHER BEHIND "MOANA."
WHICH IS ACTUALLY REALLY CRAZY
BECAUSE YOU WOULD NEVER THINK
THAT THERE WAS AN ACTUAL
CHOREOGRAPHER THAT WAS BROUGHT
YOU, YOU JUST THINK MAYBE THE
ANIMATERS DID IT.
>> RIGHT.
I ACTUALLY NEVER THOUGHT OF THAT
AS WELL, BUT I AM EXTREMELY
HUMBLED AND GRATEFUL THAT THEY
DID, BECAUSE IT'S SUCH AN
IMPORTANT FACET OF OUR CULTURE.
>> HOW DID THAT COME ABOUT?
>> I ACTUALLY WAS BROUGHT IN TO
THE DISNEY TEAM THROUGH D23 EXPO
AND I CHOREOGRAPHED THE THEME
SONG WE KNOW THE WAY.
♪ WE KNOW THE WAY ♪
>> AND THEN COME THIS YEAR
JANUARY, I WAS BROUGHT IN TO
BRING WEAPONS FOR A SONG.
♪♪
♪ ALSO I LAUGH SEE THE SUN COMES
TO STRETCH THE DAYS AND BRING
YOU FUN ♪
>> I DID THAT AND IT EVENTUALLY
LED TO OTHER SONGS AND OTHER
SCENES AND I JUST HAVE BEEN
REALLY BLESSED TO BE A PART OF
THIS.
>> WHAT IS THAT LIKE, THEN, DO
THEY BRING NUTS TO STUDIO AND
SAY, OKAY, DANCE?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> AND THEN ANIMATE YOUR MOVES
IN.
>> KIND OF.
>> I IMMEDIATE WITH THE TEAM AND
THEY EXPLAIN EVERYTHING, THE
MEANING BEHIND IT, SET UP THE
SCENE SO I UNDERSTAND, GIVE ME
REFERENCES AND BOARDS LIKE A
COMIC STRIP AND I GET TO TAKE IT
AND THE MUSIC AND THEN I GET TO
BE IN MY ELEMENT.
IN MY OWN CREATIVE SPACE.
AND THEN I CREATE A DANCE TO THE
WHOLE SONG, AND I COME BACK AND
I EXPLAIN TO THEM WHAT EACH
MOTION MEANS, HOW I WAS
INSPIRED, AND THEN I PERFORM IT
OVER AND OVER AND OVER AND OVER.
LIVE, WITH THE ANIMATERS HERE.
AND IF THEY HAVE ANY QUESTIONS,
OR THEY WANT TO SEE DIFFERENT
ANGLES I HAVE DO IT ON THE SPOT.
>> HOW LONG DOES IT TAKE TO YOU
COME UP WITH THE CHOREOGRAPHY.
IS IT HARD?
I.
>> I THINK IT'S HARD BECAUSE YOU
WILL BE YOUR WORST CRITIC,
HOWEVER, I THINK FOR ME, IT'S
DIFFERENT, BECAUSE I CONNECT
WITH THE MUSIC AND THE
VIBRATIONS AND THE LYRICS, SO
DIFFERENTLY, IT 1350EBGZ TO ME
DIFFERENT SO IT COMES YOU THE OF
MY LIMBS DIFFERENT AND THEN I
ALSO HAVE TO REMEMBER THE STORY
THAT I AM TRYING TO PORTRAY OR
IF MY ANCESTORS WERE TO WATCH
THIS IF THEY WOULD BE APPROVING
OF THIS.
SO IT'S DIFFICULT IN MANY
DIFFERENT WAYS BUT THERE IS
SOMETHING IN OUR CULTURE WE CALL
THE UT-OH AND NO OWE OH IF YOU
WERE RAISED IN THE CULTURE AND
YOU LIVED IT, AND YOU CAN SPEAKD
UNDERSTAND IT KIND OF COMES
NATURALLY.
I THINK THE ANCESTORS CHANNEL
THROUGH YOU.
I WILL HAVE SOME OF MY DANCERS
COME OUT.
>> HI.
MY BACK IS --
>> PRETTY MUCH.
>> I FEEL LIKE J-LO, YOU GUYS.
>> WE WILL DO THE FIRST MOTION,
WE GOING TO DO IS THE "MOANA."
>> THE "MOANA."
>> THAT'S A GOOD PLACE TO START.
DO OUR HANDS MIMICKING OF THE
OCEAN.
AND WE'LL SWITCH TO THE LEFT.
AND WE ARE GOING ADD OUR HIPS
SIDE TO SIDE WITH THE ROLLING OF
THE OCEAN OR THE WAVES.
AND THEN MAKE A BIG CIRCLE AND
THE HAPPENS ARE MAKING THE SHAPE
OF THE ISLAND WITH OUR HIPS AND
THEN WE ARE GOING TO DO THE
PADDLING OF THE CANOE FRONT,
BACK.
>> HERE WE GO.
THIS IS --
>> BACK.
FRONT.
BACK.
LET'S PUT IT ALTOGETHER WITH THE
DRUMS.
FIVE, SIX, FIVE, SIX, SEVEN,
EIGHT.
♪♪
>> SWITCH.
>> AND CANOE.
♪♪
>> SWITCH.
SMOLTZ ♪♪
♪♪
>> YOU DID IT.
>> YEAH.
♪♪
>> UM, --
>> NOTHING?
REALLY?
WHAT'S A DEMIGOD IT GOT TO DO?
>>> STAY TUNED FOR MORE CAREER
ADVICE WHEN WE RETURN.
♪ MADE IN HOLLYWOOD ♪
♪ú
>>> PROTIONAL CONSIDERATION
PROVIDED BY:
♪ MADE IN HOLLYWOOD ♪
>> EVER THOUGHT ABOUT A CAREER
IN CHOREOGRAPHY?
LIKE THE PROFESSIONALS ON
TODAY'S SHOW YOU MUST HAVE
ENTHUSIASM, PERSEVERANCE AND, A
GOOD ATTITUDE.
CHOREOGRAPHERS MUST ALSO BE
COLLABORATIVE BECAUSE IT TAKES
MANY ARTISTS, MUSICIANS AND
DANCERS TO CREATE A DANCE NUMBER
FOR A MOVIE.
NEVER STOP LEARNING YOUR CRAFT
BY CONTINUALLY SEEKING OUT AND
PRACTICING NEW STYLES OF DANCE.
FOR MORE INFORMATION, SEARCH
ONLINE AND VISIT WEBSITES
INCLUDING DANCESPIRIT.COM.
DANCEMAGAZINE.COM, AND
SDCWEB.ORG.
BE SURE TO CHECK WITH YOUR
PARENTS, TEACHERS, AND SCHOOL
GUIDANCE COUNSELORS TO DISCUSS
MORE CAREER OPTIONS.
>> FOR HERE BEHIND THE SCREEN
CONTENT CHECK OUT
MADEINHOLLYWOODTEEN.COM.
>> NOTE MADE IN HOLLYWOOD ♪
♪ MADE IN HOLLYWOOD ♪
♪
>>> RIGHT NOW ON "PAGE SIX
TV" -- WHY DID KANYE TAKE BACK
KIM'S $14 MILLION CHRISTMAS
PRESENT?
AND WHO'S THE MYSTERY MAN THAT
GOT J-LAW TO SAY