Hey.
Hey, honey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
This whole area here
is Donny Land.
(chuckles):
Don...
she can put her stuff
on your desk.
Well, what if I have
to tell a story?
I talk with my hands.
That's how I paint a picture.
Okay, well, maybe paint a
picture of you working. Hmm?
It'll be a one-of-a-kind.
Come on, honey,
you can put your
stuff over here.
Well, that's sweet, honey,
but, you know, I work here now;
I feel like I should
have my own desk.
I wish we could, but
if we give you a desk,
someone else is gonna
have to give theirs up.
Oh. Hmm. I see.
What?
He's your brother.
She's your wife.
I'm screwed.
Do you know what I had to do
to earn this desk?
Months of dodging
and ducking my way
through this guy's
endless stories.
(chuckles)
What are you laughing at?
I don't know.
You made fun of
Don; I liked it.
Lowell, you seem
a bit on edge.
I'm just not giving up
this desk.
It's all I have.
I'm not losing it, not today!
Hey, nobody's
gonna take your desk.
Thank you.
Okay.
Okay, you feel better now?
Yes.
It won't happen again.
Okay.
Good.
Who the flip took
my flipping pencil sharpener?!
All right,
L... Lowell,
take it easy.
I don't think you're really mad
about the pencil sharpener
or the desk.
ANDI: Maybe you're
having trouble
adjusting to being single
since you and your wife
split up.
Jeepers.
I never thought of that.
The greatest minds
in the world
have come together
to figure out the obvious!
(pencil sharpener whirring)
Is that Lowell's
pencil sharpener?
I couldn't give it back;
I was in too deep.
♪ ♪
[farmers bell]
(Driver)
Relax, it's just a bug.
That's not a bug,
that's not a bug!
(Burke)
Hit and Drone.
Seen it, covered it.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
(stage bell rings)
Hiyeeeeeee!
Oh! We all just got new
smartphones at Cricket!
(phone rings)
Hiyeeeeeee!
!Holaaaaa!
OK, biyeeeeee!
Biyeeeee!!
Ever since Darrell's family
started using Gain Flings,
their laundry smells more
amazing than ever.
Uh, honey, isn't that the dog's
towel?
Hey, mi towel, su towel.
There's more Gain scent plus Oxi
Boost
and Febreze odor remover in
every Gain Fling.
Gain. Seriously Good Scent.
If you love the scent of Gain
Flings,
you'll love our scent beads
and dish soap too.
Brushing only reaches
25% of your mouth.
LISTERINE® cleans
virtually 100%.
Helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%.
Always go for 100.
Bring Out the Bold™
For mild-to-moderate eczema,
there's EUCRISA.
It's steroid-free.
Do not use if you are allergic
to EUCRISA or its ingredients.
Allergic reactions may occur
at or near the application site.
The most common side effect
is application site pain.
Ask your doctor about EUCRISA.
Mom, I have to build a solar
system for my science class.
Again?
You already know this stuff.
How many planets are
in the solar system?
A billion.
Two?
(clears throat)
Okay, we'll work on it
this weekend.
It's due tomorrow.
Of course it is.
Okay, well, I-I'll get your dad
to do it when he gets home.
Oh, you know what'll be fun?
I'll say we told him
about it last week.
(door opens)
Hey, guys.
Hi.
(chuckles)
So, get this.
Lowell placed an order
with the lumberyard today,
and he got all weepy
when they asked
if we were doing
his-and-hers closets.
He is getting
really good prices, though.
He's too lonely, all by himself
in that apartment.
I got to stop by there
and, well,
see if I can snap him out of it.
Tonight?
Mm-hmm.
(hissing inhale)
But...
last week you promised Teddy
you'd build him a solar system.
I know.
I remember.
I listen.
But shouldn't you do this one?
I mean, last night
I had to clean dog poop
off of Emme's shoe, again.
I think she
just jumps from pile to pile.
Well, while you
were cleaning her shoes,
I hemmed Kate's band uniform
to make it shorter.
Longer.
I made it longer,
like a pilgrim.
All right,
forget Lowell--
I'll do the solar system.
I already got it all
planned out, because I've
been thinking about ever since
you mentioned it last week.
No. I like that you want
to go check on your friend,
so I will create the universe.
A woman probably did it anyway.
Man, you guys are too busy.
The only thing I did last night
was binge-watch Fantasy Island.
And all I can say is,
be careful what you wish for.
Heh. That sounds
like a night, huh?
Hmm.
Mindless, pointless fun?
Do you remember
how much fun fun was?
Yeah.
You know, sometimes I
see old pictures of us,
and I think: What are
they smiling about?
Don't they know
what's coming?
Right?
LOWELL:
I'm so glad you dropped by.
Yeah.
Let me just close
my bedroom door.
Well, now the place
looks huge.
Can you hear me over there?
Sit down, make
yourself at home.
(sighs)
This is cozy.
(chuckles)
The saleslady at the store
said it was a love seat.
Then I said,
"I love you, too."
Then I kind of
had to buy it.
Look, Lowell,
I know you're going through
a tough time, but...
your mood is creating
a weird work vibe.
Is it the crying?
The yelling?
I think it's the combo platter,
my friend.
Oh, come on,
it's not all bad.
You got your own place here.
You could do whatever you want.
Like what?
That is a great question.
Uh, well, what were you doing
before I got here?
Well, I open and close
the bed a lot.
(knocking at door)
Fun. (chuckles)
Hey, Don. Don's here.
He'll lighten things up.
Don, lighten things up.
What brings you by,
fair traveler?
Well, I went home,
and you know what I realized?
My wife lives there.
So, I, uh,
grabbed some beer and snacks,
and here I am.
See, Lowell?
It's all coming together.
We got food,
we got beverages.
Now we just need something
to do... besides talking.
Hey. What's this hole?
I tried to hang a picture, but
I was madder than I thought.
Well, I think we
can do something with that.
That's my light bill.
No, no, we'll make
a game out of this.
Okay, if you get the ball
in the hole from here,
that's one point.
And if you make it from here,
it's two points.
Ah.
And if you
don't get in the hole,
it's no points.
All right,
I like that you're trying.
Yes!
Nothin' but hole.
This is so fun!
But we lost the ball;
now what do we do?
Dang it, Adam!
Automatic ball return.
Gentlemen, I think
we just invented a sport.
This is a masterpiece.
This is definitely gonna make
the front table at open house.
(chuckles):
Yeah. It looks good.
So, is it time to paint Uranus?
Teddy, you've been
doing that all night.
You're right. I'm sorry.
(sighs) But Uranus has
a weird bump on it.
Miss it.
Miss it. Mi...
Yes!
(groans)
(chuckles)
What are you doing, Don?
Follow through!
All right, good game.
I should get going
and help with Teddy's project.
I'm glad you're
feeling better, Lowell.
This was surprisingly fun.
It really was.
I mean, you invented a game
you can only play
in my apartment.
Mm-hmm.
That makes me the hub.
I'm the hub of the wheel.
You can't leave.
I demand a rematch.
Well, I would, because I am at
the peak of my athletic ability,
but I should get home.
Okay, then
tomorrow.
Well...
Andi's not gonna let me
come back tomorrow.
I have responsibilities.
Who knows what
she told me last week
that I'm supposed
to do tomorrow?
Okay, fine. Then
we'll-we'll play without you.
What?
You're gonna have fun
without me?
Probably more.
All you really need is the hub.
But...
but I invented the game.
Well, we'll put up a
picture in your memory.
No, no, no.
I'm coming back.
I just have to figure out a way
to work it with Andi.
She only let me come down here
because Lowell's
such a basket case.
Thanks.
Oh. No, that's a...
that's a good thing.
I can use that.
Oh. Then you're welcome.
So, how's Lowell doing?
It is no fun over there,
let me tell ya.
I even had
to bring Don in to help.
And Lowell wants me to come back
again tomorrow, but...
Hmm.
I couldn't do that.
Could I?
Maybe you should bring him
over here.
That... is an idea
I did not see coming.
Oh, but, no,
I'm afraid it'd remind him
of everything
he used to have...
You know what?
He'll be fine.
The hell with him.
Oh, no, no.
Wait a minute.
I mean, he's your friend.
You need to be there for him.
You should go back tomorrow.
Wha...
(groans)
Well, if you're
gonna force me to,
fine, I'll go.
When will I ever get
a minute for myself?
[music playing]
(VO)
This is Jerry.
Jerry has a
membership to this gym,
but he's not using it.
And he has subscriptions to a
music service he doesn't listen
to and five streaming video
services he doesn't watch.
This is Jerry learning that
he's still paying for this stuff
he's not using.
He's seeing his recurring
payments in Control Tower
in the Wells Fargo Mobile app.
This is Jerry canceling
a few things. Booyah.
This is Jerry appreciating the
people who made this possible.
Oh look, there they are.
(Team Member)
This is Wells Fargo.
New Whole Blends Ginger
Recovery.
Blended with purpose, for
fragile hair.
With revitalizing ginger, known
to recover strength,
and golden honey.
As a whole blend,
it provides twice the breakage
protection.
To make hair stronger instantly.
Blended makes us better.
Whole Blends.
By Garnier, naturally.
♪ ♪
♪ Step it up. ♪
♪ Always take the risk. ♪
Don't just watch it...
Put your phone down and do it.
♪ Drip splash like the ice
on the wrist. ♪
♪ Brrt brrt brrt brrt ♪
♪ that's a call I can't miss. ♪
Let's do.
Why LensCrafters?
Personalized service is why.
Clarifye Digital
Eye Exam is why.
Eyeglasses with prescription
lenses starting at $99.
Lenscrafters Is Why.
Book an eye exam today.
I love my babies,
love my boys.
Since I'm a truck driver,
you know there's times
that I'm gone for,
like, three weeks at a time.
Even if I'm 3,000 miles away,
I'm connected with my boys.
Every day I can
video chat with them.
I could be in the middle
of Wyoming.
Even if I'm like waaay...
out here,
I can still reach my kids.
Baby, you-- you see me?
(sons)
Hey, Daddy!
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now comes with Apple Music on us
and $300 off our best phones.
Only on Verizon.
So, check out
this standing desk.
It takes up less space
than a regular desk,
and then if you're sitting,
I can hover right over you.
Uh-huh.
L-Let's keep thinking.
There's just no room in here.
I can't hang you
from the ceiling like a bat.
I can't believe this. My pencil
sharpener's missing again.
Don, cough it up.
Fine.
But you should know I sharpened
a carrot in here earlier,
so it may be a little slow.
Sharpen whatever you want, Don.
What's mine is yours.
Hey, Lowell seems better.
Mm-hmm.
I guess you get to stay home
with me tonight.
Great. What a happy surprise.
All right, well, I have to go
fill out these purchase orders,
so I guess I'll go do it
in the shovel of the bulldozer.
If they raise me up, it'll be
like a penthouse office.
What are you doing, man?
Sad it up.
If Andi doesn't think you're
a mess, my game nights are over.
Well, I don't want that.
When you're not there,
Don cheats.
Every time I try to shoot,
he tickles me.
Victory at any cost.
That's what makes a champion.
My pen fell in the engine.
(chuckles)
I hope that's gonna be okay.
Uh, Lowell, I'm just gonna
borrow one of yours.
Oh, Lowell won't mind.
Right, Lowell?
I do mind.
How dare you?
What?
Why is everybody always
taking my stuff?
You just said y-your
stuff was our stuff.
Feelings don't make sense, Andi.
I'm gonna go find a church
and get some soup.
What happened?
I thought he was better.
Looks like I'm gonna have to go
back over there again tonight.
(groans)
You know what, Adam?
I don't believe you.
You don't?
It's just, you've grown
so much as a person,
I mean, putting your friends
before yourself.
I-I, it... I'm so proud of you.
Oh.
Thanks, honey.
(chuckles)
Aww. Mm.
For tonight's match,
I created a signature cocktail
to enjoy during warm-ups.
Oh.
We are getting real classy.
Hey, you know, this could
be a rich guy sport,
like polo
or non-miniature golfing.
Yeah, this could
really catch on.
Uh, but we need a name first.
You don't get on ESPN
without a name.
I like "Wall Ball."
Eh, too rhymey.
We don't want that crowd.
Hmm.
How about "Wall Hole"?
I like it. It tells a story.
Oh, then we can call
my signature drink
an Andy Wall-Hole.
Uh, no, I don't get it.
Well, you know,
like Andy Warhol.
Ah.
Who's that?
Don. Andy Warhol?
From New York?
Plays shortstop for the Mets?
Oh, right, right. Okay.
Ah. Hey, Lowell, see if anyone
owns the name WallHoleUSA.com.
Yeah, we're definitely gonna
want that for the online store.
The money is in the merchandise.
Someone already has
the Wall Hole site,
but the subject matter's
quite disturbing.
Ooh, she was not expecting that.
Oh-- well, maybe she was.
(knocking on door)
Hey, Dad.
Hey.
Dad, what are you doing here?
You're supposed to be home
resting from your knee surgery.
Well, we heard from Don that
you boys had something good
going on over here, so I told
your mother that my nurse, uh...
Oh, my name is Funchy.
You can just call me that.
Sure thing, Nursey.
Said I should get out of
the house and take a rehab walk.
So, uh, what's going on?
I hope you're throwing something
into that hole.
We need to talk to you.
What's going on?
You tell us. Our husbands
have been over at Lowell's
apartment every night this week.
What are they up to?
They're not up to anything.
They're helping Lowell
during a difficult time.
I'm actually very proud of them.
Bless her little heart.
No, i-it's true.
I-- you should be happy.
Our husbands are good people.
I highly doubt that.
Something's in it for them,
or else they wouldn't
be over there.
No.
Well...
That does sound more like Adam.
Shoot. You know,
I really thought
he was growing as a person.
Honey, they don't do that.
LOWELL:
All right.
We're at match point.
For the first time
in the history of Wall Hole,
a father and son meet
in the playoffs.
Can a family
survive it?
(groans)
All right.
Yeah!
Dad makes it to the finals.
Even on one leg,
the old man smoked you.
He gets in my head.
I built that head.
I know my way around in there.
Well, I've got winner.
You know, I was getting
burned out on nursing,
but now that I'm a pro athlete,
I've got my passion back.
(phone ringing)
Ooh, it's Andi.
Uh, everybody shush.
Well, we're starting
a game here.
Look, if I go down,
we all go down.
Uh, how exactly will I go down?
Well, I--
Just, everybody, shush.
Hey, honey.
No, Lowell's not doing so good.
Friday was his and Jen's
movie night,
so it's bringing up
a lot of feelings.
I think we're gonna watch
all the Harry Potters.
Okay, bye, honey.
(chuckles)
Andi has no idea.
It's game on, boys.
(laughter)
Well, he's terrible at this.
He didn't even hang up before
he said "Andi has no idea."
So what's our move?
All I can say is, I've had
pepper spray in my purse
for four years, and I want
to use it before it expires.
That'll be the pizza.
Ooh.
All right.
Uh, oh.
I can't believe that Lowell
started feeling better
this very minute.
I say we all go home
to our beautiful wives. Huh?
Oh, hey, ladies.
(chuckles)
Didn't see you there.
Yes, I lied about why
I was at Lowell's.
But you ambushed me before
I could cover it up.
So who's really at fault?
You used your friend's
unhappiness
to go out and have fun
and avoid stuff around here.
What? No. I love the
stuff around here.
Or were you trying to avoid me?
No. No.
It was the stuff around here.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, you're making up reasons
to go out at night,
and... and... you don't want me
to have a desk at work.
Yeah. It's starting
to come together now,
it's all connected.
No, no, stop connecting things.
Okay? H-Honey, I swear,
this is just about me trying to
get away with something silly.
Well, then,
what's really going on?
Okay, fine. Look-- uh...
I was just trying
to enjoy a little break.
But not from you.
There's school projects
and shoes that need
de-poopifying, and...
and the kids never
turn off a light.
I have probably spent
three years of my life
turning off lights.
I mean, you have to know
what I'm talking about.
No, I don't.
I find every minute
with my children
to be a joy to treasure.
Do you?
(mouths)
Two weeks ago, when you went to
Target to buy Teddy new shorts?
Mm-hmm.
You were gone so
long, I got worried.
Yeah. So I went down there.
And you know who I saw,
drinking an Icee,
watching Dr. Phil
in the TV section?
My long-lost twin sister?
No, it was you, baby.
But I didn't say anything.
I left and let you have
your time because I get it.
And also, to keep in my pocket
in case something
like this came up.
Well, I'm very sorry...
that you found out about that.
You know, we do spend
a lot of time
taking care of other people.
That's all I'm saying.
And since we're coming clean,
I should tell you that time
at Target, it wasn't my first.
They know me there.
They let me use the remote
that controls all 65 TVs.
There's a master remote?
Uh-huh.
How big is it? I need
to know how big it is.
Eh, it's not big,
but it's heavy.
(laughs):
Nice.
Yeah.
You see?
Everyone needs to bust
out once in a while.
My mistake was not
busting you out with me.
Aw, that's sweet.
And, you know, maybe I should've
taken you with me
to watch the 65 TVs.
I would like to check
out that remote.
You know, Target's open
for another hour.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
Oh, h-hey, kids, uh,
we're going out to run some
very important adult errands.
Pro tip, if you angle the TVs
just right,
you can watch it
from the bed department.
I am so glad I married you.
Hmm.
I landed.
I saw my leg did not look right.
I was just finishing a ride.
I felt this awful pain in my
chest.
I had a PE blood clot in my
lung.
I was scared.
I had a DVT blood clot.
Having one really puts you in
danger of having another.
My doctor and I chose XARELTO®.
XARELTO®. To help keep me
protected.
XARELTO® is a latest-generation
blood thinner that's...
proven to treat and reduce the
risk of DVT
or PE blood clots from happening
again.
In clinical studies, almost 98%
of patients on
XARELTO® did not experience
another DVT or PE.
XARELTO® works differently.
Warfarin interferes with at
least 6 of your body's
natural blood-clotting factors.
XARELTO® is selective, targeting
just one critical factor.
Don't stop taking XARELTO®
without talking to your doctor,
as this may increase risk of
blood clots.
While taking, you may bruise
more easily,
or take longer for bleeding to
stop.
XARELTO® can cause serious, and
in rare cases, fatal bleeding.
It may increase your risk of
bleeding
if you take certain medicines.
Get help right away for
unexpected
bleeding or unusual bruising.
Do not take XARELTO®
if you have an artificial heart
valve or abnormal bleeding.
Before starting,
tell your doctor about all
planned medical
or dental procedures and any
kidney or liver problems.
Learn all you can...
to help protect yourself from
another DVT or PE.
Talk to your doctor about
XARELTO®.
I can't believe it.
That there's a lobster
in our hot tub?
Lobster: Oh, you guys.
There's a jet!
Oh...I needed this.
No, I can't believe how
easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
our car insurance with GEICO.
We could have been doing
this a long time ago.
So, you guys staying
at the hotel?
Yeah, we just got married.
Oh ho-ho! Congratulations!
Thank you.
Yeah, I'm afraid of
commitment...
and being boiled alive.
Oh, shoot.
Believe it.
GEICO could save you 15% or more
on car insurance.
That guy's the worst.
Still fresh...
♪
Unstopables In-Wash Scent
Booster
♪
Downy Unstopables
Why shop Marshalls?
Because...
Their prices will thrill you.
Whoo-hoo!
The brands will surprise you.
Mwah!
And every trip feels
like an instant victory.
Woman:
Marshalls.
Never boring.
Always surprising.
Good morning, guys.
Woman:
MHey, morning, honey.
Andi, I know you were upset
with Adam, but this week,
I started to enjoy my new life.
Having the guys there
really did help.
Go tell that to Marcy.
I had to sleep
on the porch swing last night.
Don't worry, Lowell.
Adam and I are good.
All right, well,
I have some paperwork to do,
so if you need me,
I'll be in my bulldozer.
Oh, whoa, whoa, why
would you go out there,
when you can
just do your work here
on your new desk?
Whoa.
Yeah.
I invented the Murphy desk.
The Murphy bed's
hardworking little brother.
Oh, I love it.
Now I'm officially part
of the team.
Thanks, honey.
Hmm, yeah. Wall hole, wall desk.
Man, the "wall" part of my brain
is really firing right now.