XI JINPING HERE, THEIR GUY HERE,
APPEARED POTUS SAYS, NOPE, I'M
OUT OF HERE, SEE YOU ON THE 9th
HOLE
SO IT'S TAKING LONGER THAN
EXPECTED BECAUSE THE CHINESE
WANT TO IRON OUT ALL OF THE
AGREEMENTS IN WRITING IN DETAIL
VERY, VERY CAREFULLY BEFORE THEY
SEND XI JINPING TO A HIGH-STAKES
FACE-TO-FACE MEETING HERE IN THE
UNITED STATES.
>> EAMON JAVERS IN D.C
MIKE, ON A WEEK WHERE WE HAVE
OPTIMISM ON THAT DEAL AT LEAST
NOT IMPROVE, WE'RE DOWN 2% FOR
THE WEEK.
>> THE MARKET MAY BE LOSING A
LITTLE BIT OF PATIENT RIGHT NOW,
BUT THE GOOD NEWS IS WE'RE DOWN
2% SO MAYBE WE HAVE NO LONGER
PRICED IN A GOOD SCENARIO.
>> THE PRESIDENT SAID THAT THE
MARKET WOULD SPIKE ON A TRADE
DEAL TODAY.
>> THANKS FOR WATCHING TODAY AND
ALL WEEK
THAT DOES IT FOR "CLOSING BELL."
>> HAVE A GREAT WEEKEND.
>>> SARA, "FAST MONEY" DOES
BEGIN RIGHT NOW LIVE FROM THE
NASDAQ MARKET SITE
I'M SCOTT WAPNER IN TONIGHT FOR
MELISSA LEE.
TONIGHT WE HAVE THE CEO OF
TAKETWO ENTERTAINMENT, STRAUSS
ZELNICK HERE TO TALK ABOUT HIS
BIG PUSH INTO E-SPORTS AS THEY
HOSTED THEIR DRAFT THIS WEEK
WE DO START WITH THE GLOBAL
GROWTH FEARS GRIPPING WALL
STREET
THE DOW DOWN 200 POINTS AT THE
LOWS
REBOUNDED NICELY AT THE CLOSE.
CHINA GOT SLAMMED OVERNIGHT, THE
U.S. ADDED ONLY 20,000 JOBS IN
FEBRUARY, WORST WEEK OF THE YEAR
FOR STOCKS, AS WE MARK THE
TEN-YEAR ANNIVERSARY OF THE BULL
MARKET
CAME CLOSE TO DYING THIS FALL.
AS GROWTH SLOWS AROUND THE
GLOBE, THE BULL LOOKS LIKE IT
COULD BE IN FOR ANOTHER BEAR
SCARE.
HOW WORRIED SHOULD INVESTORS BE?
TIM, I LEAD YOU WITH THAT
BREAKING NEWS THAT THESE TRADE
TALKS ARE TAKING LONGER THAN
EXPECTED
WHO COULD HAVE THOUGHT THAT?
>> WELL, I THINK I HEAR SOME
SARCASM, SCOTT
IF YOU THROW TRADE DYSFUNCTION
INTO THE MIDDLE OF A MARKET
GETTING GROWTH SIGNALS THAT ARE
VERY DIFFICULT, HEADLINE ON
TODAY'S PAYROLL NUMBER WAS
SHOCKING
IF YOU LOOK BELOW THE SURFACE,
IT WASN'T THAT BAD
THERE ARE SOME IRREGULARITY THE
IN THE DATA FLOW THE LAST COUPLE
OF MONTHS.
THE CHINESE DATA, SHOULD WE BE
SURPRISED THEIR EXPORTS FELL
THE LAST SEVEN DAYS WE'VE SEEN
CREDIT BEGIN TO DETERIORATE.
WHAT WAS THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
THE PULL-BACK IN OCTOBER AND
DECEMBER FROM THAT EARLIER IN
THE YEAR
IT WAS THAT WE SAW CDX, CREDIT,
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO MEASURE,
LOOK AT THE HYG IS ONE WAY TO DO
IT
BOTTOM LINE, THE MARKET CLOSED
ON THE HIGHS AND THAT'S VERY
IMPRESSIVE
IN FACT I THINK THAT CHANGED
SENTIMENT A LOT.
>> DANNY, WHAT ARE WE TO MAKE OF
THAT BREAKING NEWS
>> THIS MORNING IT LOOKS LIKE
INVESTORS WERE TAKING ALL THE
GROWTH FEARS AND ALL THE
POTENTIAL FOR A PUSHED-OUT DEAL
PRETTY SERIOUSLY
CRUDE OIL WAS DOWN 3.5%.
THE 10-YEAR TREASURY YIELD
ALMOST TOUCHED 2.60.
NIKKEI DOWN 2%
THAT SEEMED LIKE RISK ALL KIND
OF STUFF
WE HAD THIS SLOW BURN UP SINCE
THE DECEMBER LOWS.
I THINK TIM IS 100% RIGHT.
THE FACT THAT WE ONLY CLOSED
DOWN 20 IN THE S&P AND CRUDE
MADE UP A LOT OF ROOM, THE FACT
THE 10-YEAR TREASURY YIELD DID
NOT CLOSE SITTING ON THAT
TECHNICAL LEVEL, I THINK IT'S
OKAY
THAT BEING SAID, I JUST DON'T
KNOW WHAT THE CATALYSTS ARE
RIGHT NOW.
>> I THINK IT WAS MORE A
QUESTION ABOUT GOING INTO THE
WEEKEND WITHOUT A CHINA DEAL
THAT'S DONE.
MAYBE THERE WAS A RISK TO THE
UPSIDE
YOU KNOW THERE'S GOING TO BE A
LAST GASP BOUNCE ONCE THEY GET A
CHINA DEAL.
>> MAYBE
>> I THINK IT'S BEEN A
LEGITIMATE QUESTION --
>> I THINK YOU'LL GET IT, IT'S
HOW LONG LASTING WILL IT BE, HOW
QUICK WILL IT BE SOLD.
COMING FROM THIS LEVEL I DON'T
THINK IT'S GOING TO BE THAT
AGGRESSIVE
NONETHELESS, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
SELL IT A WEEKEND AHEAD OF A
POTENTIAL DEAL.
>> YOU HAD THAT FLARE-UP IN THE
LOW, THE GAP IN THE FUTURES WAS
EXCEEDINGLY RARE AND WE'VE BEEN
DOWN SINCE
HOW MUCH IS THIS
MAYBE THE SELL-OFF AND RECOVERY
NEGATE EACH OTHER AND WE'RE
BASICALLY WHERE WE WERE IN
OCTOBER SINCE THINGS STARTED
GETTING QUESTIONING AND SINCE
ALL THE DATA HAS GOTTEN WORSE.
>> ZERO GROWTH
I KNOW TIM BRINGS UP GREAT
POINTS ABOUT WHY IT'S NOT AS
NEGATIVE AS IT SEEMS TO ME OR ON
THIS SIDE OF THE DESK, I DON'T
WANT TO SPEAK FOR YOU, BUT
THERE'S ZERO GROWTH BASICALLY IN
GERMANY.
ITALY IS IN RECESSION.
THERE'S NO GROWTH IN JAPAN
THE ECB PROBABLY OVERESTIMATED
WHEREVER THEY THINK GDP IS GOING
TO BE.
THE ECB IS OUT OF BULLETS.
JAPAN IS OUT OF BULLETS.
EVERYONE IS OUT OF BULLETS
EXEMPT FOR US, AND WE DON'T HAVE
THAT MANY BULL ETS IN CASE OF A
DOWNTURN
I THINK THAT THE MARKET IS
HAVING A DAY OF RECKONING.
>> IF YOU WANT TO LOOK AT THIS
WEEK, THIS WAS A BEARISH
REVERSAL WEEK.
I THINK WE'VE BEEN LEADING TO
THIS FOR A LONG TIME
CARTER SAYS WE'RE BACK TO WHERE
WE WERE.
ONE OF THE THINGS I'VE SAID AND
I SAID THIS IN THE FALL, I THINK
Q1 2019 COULD BE Q1 2016-LIKE.
I THINK WE GOT OUR MARKET
DISLOCATION A LITTLE BEFORE
THIS
SO TEND TO AGREE WITH WHAT
CARTER SAID, BUT I JUST DON'T
SEE THE DATA FALLING APART THAT
QUICKLY.
AGAIN, LET'S TALK ABOUT U.S.
DATA
ALTHOUGH THIS IS A TERRIBLE
HEADLINE PRINT --
>> IT'S PROBABLY AN ANOMALY.
THE MARKET OBVIOUSLY IS PLACING
ITS BETS.
>> THE CONSUMER IS NOT DEAD.
>> YEAH, BUT TIM, HERE'S THE
THING.
THE DATA IS NOT GOOD AND IT'S
NOT GETTING BETTER IN CHINA AND
IT'S NOT GOOD AND IT'S NOT
GETTING BETTER IN EUROPE
THE THING THAT I WOULD BE
WORRIED ABOUT AFTER THIS STRONG
REFLEX IS WE GET INTO MID-APRIL
AND START HAVING Q1 EARNINGS AND
FORWARD GUIDANCE AND SEE REALLY
LIGHT GUIDANCE
THAT'S THE SORT OF THING THAT I
THINK WOULD REALLY SHAKE MARKET
PARTICIPANTS.
>> HAVEN'T WE RESET GUIDANCE A
BIT?
IT SEEMS LIKE NO ONE IS
EXPECTING ANYTHING ANYMORE
>> THEY'RE NOT WORRIED BECAUSE
THE RICOCHET DREW IN A LOT OF
MONEY AND EMBOLDENED PEOPLE TO
THINK IT NEVER HAPPENED, THE
DECEMBER THING WASN'T REAL, AND
WE KNOW IT WAS REAL.
>> THE CONVERSATIONS THAT I HAVE
WITH ACTIVE MONEY MANAGERS AND
PIERS ON THE STREET IS THAT
PEOPLE ARE NOT DOING WELL IN
THIS MARKET.
>> I UNDERSTAND --
>> I DON'T THINK PEOPLE ARE
COMPLACENT IS MY POINT.
>> I UNDERSTAND THE ANALOGY TO
2015-16 BUT WE WERE IN A GLOBAL
EASING ENVIRONMENT BACK IN
2015-16, ESPECIALLY IN THE
EUROZONE
WHERE ARE THEY GOING TO BE
EASING FROM?
WHERE ARE THEY GOING TO EASE
FROM
THEY DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY.
>> ACTUALLY, STEVE, WE STARTED
TIGHTENING
THE FED'S FIRST RATE HIKE WAS IN
DECEMBER.
>> BUT THAT'S OFF THE TABLE.
>> BUT THE FED WAS GOING TO PUSH
THE WORLD INTO A GLOBAL
RECESSION.
THIS IS THE EXACT SAME
CONDITIONS.
>> BUT EUROPE, THIS IS THE MAIN
CONCERN WHERE EVERYONE, EVEN
PEOPLE THAT SAY THEY'RE BEARISH
SAY THEY'RE MORE BULLISH ON
AMERICA VERSUS EUROPE, BUT
EUROPE WAS ON A STRING OF EASING
FOR FOUR YEARS AND IT GOT THEM
NO PLACE
>> THE KEY DATA POINT IN THE
PA
MARKET IS THERE'S ONE SECTOR
THAT'S MAKING ALL-TIME HIGHS
WELL, TWO.
S&P MIDCAP UTILITIES AND S&P
500.
>> I WAS GOING TO BRING UP THE
FACT THAT YOU HAVE THE
TRANSPORTS AND THE RUSSELL
NOW, THE RUSSELL HAD A NICE
COMEBACK TODAY ALONG WITH
EVERYTHING ELSE, BUT THE TREND
IS NOT YOUR FRIEND IF YOU'RE
LOOKING AT DOW THEORY THROUGH
TRANSPORTS AND SMALL CAPS LEADS
YOU DOWN, LEADS YOU UP
THEY'RE NOT PERFORMING WELL.
>> SMALL CAPS HAVE LED US HERE
AND THE SEMIS WERE THE FIRST TO
ROLL
MAYBE IT'S LIKE IT WAS BACK IN
JUNE, LET'S WAIT AND SEE
FOLKS, IS THERE ANY SURPRISE,
MARKETS HAVE DONE NOTHING FOR 15
MONTHS
I MEAN THIS ISN'T REALLY -- WITH
A LOT OF VOLATILITY IN BETWEEN
SO I APPRECIATE THE FACT WE'RE
ALL GNASHING OUR TEETH RIGHT
NOW.
>> IF YOU SAY OKAY, WE CANCELLED
OURSELVES OUT, DECEMBER DOWN,
NOW WE'RE UP
NOW ARE WE AT THE INFLECTION
POINT?
YOU NEED SOMETHING DRAMATIC TO
HAPPEN --
>> EPS GOING NEGATIVE, MARGINS
HAVE PEAKED AND GDP IS FALLING
IS THAT A SPOT YOU WANT TO PUT
NEW MONEY TO WORK?
>> THE DIXIE OR DOLLAR INDEX
ALMOST BROKE OUT TO A 52-WEEK
HIGH
IF IT WERE TO DO THAT AT A TIME
COMMODITY PRICES ARE PRETTY
FIRM, SO THAT COMBINATION TO ME
WITH RATES GOING DOWN FOR THE
WRONG REASONS, NOT A GREAT
COMBINATION FOR STOCKS RIGHT
NOW.
>> JUST AS WE GET SET THIS
WEEKEND TO MARK THE 10-YEAR
ANNIVERSARY OF THE BULL MARKET,
THIS CONVERSATION IS WONDERING
WHEN IT'S GOING TO END
THE MARKETS ARE BATTLING SOME
KEY TECHNICAL LEVELS
DON'T WORRY, THE CHART MASTER
WILL TELL US WHAT IT ALL MEANS
WHY DON'T YOU GO TO THE PLASMA
AND SHOW US.
>> ON THE WAY TO THE PLASMA,
LET'S NOTE THAT THE NASDAQ
COMPOSITE DROPPED 24%, THE S&P
DROPPED MORE THAN 20%.
WE'VE HAD A BEAR MARKET.
NOW THE QUESTION IS WHETHER
WE'RE RECOVERING AND GOING TO
MAKE NEW HIGHS OR THIS IMPETUOUS
BOUNCE IS JUST THAT, A BOUNCE.
NO LINES OR DRAWINGS BY ME
LET'S PUT IN A FEW AND SEE WHAT
WE CAN FIGURE OUT.
HERE'S A CHART OF THE S&P.
WHAT WE KNOW IS, AGAIN, WHILE
THE 2800 LEVEL IS CITED, THAT'S
NOT THE LEVEL THAT HAS MATTERED
FOR THE MARKET
WE'VE HAD THREE WELL-DEFINED
INTERMEDIATE TOPS.
2817, 2815, 2815
THE MARKET HIT THAT LEVEL
EXACTLY LAST WEEK AFTER NEWS ON
THE TRADE FRONT AND HAS PIVOTED
STRAIGHT DOWN.
WE KNOW THE TRANSPORTS JUST HAD
A RECORD SEQUENCE OF LOSSES.
AND SO IS IT JUST A BOUNCE
A COUPLE OF WAYS TO DRAW THE
LINES.
ON THE WAY UP WE HAVE HAD FOUR
DISTINCT PULLBACKS
THERE WAS A 3%, THIS WAS 2.3,
THIS IS 2.1 AND THIS IS 3.1.
THE BULL WOULD SAY THAT'S JUST A
NORMAL GIVE-BACK AND WE'RE ON
OUR WAY TO DOING THINGS LIKE
THAT
MY HUNCH IS OTHERWISE.
I THINK ULTIMATELY WE STILL HAVE
A LOT OF RISK TO THE DOWNSIDE
AND AT A MINIMUM WE'RE LIKELY TO
FIND A REFERENCE POINT AS WE
FOUND BEFORE HERE, JUST AS WE
HAD REFERENCE POINTS AT THE HIGH
AT 2800.
AND THAT A NORMAL CHECK BACK IS
NOT GOING TO BE 3% AFTER
ADVANCING 20, BUT IT'S MORE LIKE
7, 8, 9, WHICH WOULD GET US DOWN
TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS CHANNEL.
AND I THINK THAT ULTIMATELY IS
WHAT HAS TO BE CONSIDERED BEFORE
ONE COULD THINK ABOUT PUTTING
MONEY TO WORK BECAUSE WE'VE
DIPPED
WE HAVEN'T DIPPED AT ALL
WE'VE GONE DOWN 3% AND THAT IS
NOTHING.
>> SO, CARTER, I THOUGHT THAT WE
WERE GOING TO RECHECK THOSE LOWS
THAT WE SAW, THE 2350 RANGE.
I AGREE WITH YOU, I THINK IT'S
MORE LIKE 5% OR 7% DOWN FROM
HERE
IS THERE ANY SHOT IN YOUR MIND,
I KNOW THERE'S ALWAYS A SHOT, SO
HOW CREDIBLE IS ANOTHER SHOT
DOWN TO 2350
>> I THINK IT'S THE BEST BET YOU
CAN MAKE
THIS IS A MINIMUM.
THE REAL QUESTION IS DO WE --
NOW, IT'S IMPORTANT, PEOPLE USE
THE WORD "RETEST."
IT WOULD BE A TEST
IF YOU HAVE A LOW AND YOU GO
BACK THERE YOU'RE TESTING IT
IF YOU GO BACK A SECOND TIME,
YOU'RE RETESTING IT.
DO WE TEST THE LOWS?
I THINK WE DO.
>> THE BEST BET WE CAN MAKE IS
THAT WE'RE GOING BACK TO RETEST
THE LOWS
THAT'S WHAT I JUST HEARD YOU
SAY?
>> SURE.
>> THAT'S A LITTLE UNSETTLING ON
THIS FRIDAY EVENING.
>> REMEMBER, THE MARKET DIDN'T
PEAK IN SEPTEMBER, OCTOBER
THAT WAS A FAKE NEW HIGH
INDUSTRIALS PEAKED IN JANUARY OF
2018.
>> CARTER --
>> MATERIALS PEAKED IN '18,
ENERGY PEAKED.
IT WAS ONLY THE S&P, BECAUSE
FAANG HAD THAT HEAD FAKE, GLOBAL
EQUITIES, ALL OF THEM ALL PEAKED
OVER A YEAR AGO AND THEY HAVE
NEVER GOTTEN BETTER.
>> CARTER, WE TALK FUNDAMENTALS
SO LET'S JUST TALK CHARTS
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE THERE
TO DO.
>> I CAN DO BOTH IF YOU'D LIKE.
>> WE'VE SEEN THIS V BEFORE.
>> DOES HE LOOK LIKE A ONE-TRICK
PONY TO YOU?
>> CARTER, IF I WAS GOING TO
DRAFT A TEAM RIGHT NOW, HE WOULD
BE THE BEST PERSON AVAILABLE IF
I MISSPOKE
HAVEN'T WE SEEN THIS V BEFORE,
CARTER
WE'VE SEEN Vs OF 5%, OF 7%
THESE HAVEN'T BEEN Ws, THEY HAVE
BEEN Vs.
I HAD A CONVERSATION WITH A
CLIENT ABOUT THAT TODAY.
I THINK THAT'S A FAIR POINT.
>> WELL, YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
THIS KIND OF THING HOW MANY REAL
Vs ARE THERE IN TERMS OF
DRAWDOWNS IN THE S&P OF 15%,
20%.
>> WE KNOW THIS WAS HISTORIC
I'M NOT SAYING THIS IS LIKE
ANYTHING WE'VE SEEN.
BUT I'M SAYING IN THE LAST TEN
YEARS, WE'VE SEEN THESE MOMENTS
WHERE THE MARKET HAS BEEN RIGHT
HERE ON A PROPORTIONATE BASIS
LOWER, BUT CLEARLY A MOMENT
WHERE WE THOUGHT THIS WAS IT.
>> YEAH.
AGAIN, I WOULD SAY LOOK AT THE
MESSAGE OF UTILITIES,THE FACT
RATES ARE DOING WHAT THEY'RE
DOING, FINANCIALS ARE NOT
WORKING AND THAT WORSE THAN
ANYTHING, IT WAS TOO STEEP
IF WE SPENT SOME TIME HEALING
AFTER THE CHRISTMAS LOW AND
WORKING THROUGH IT, THE FACT
THAT IT HAPPENED SO QUICKLY IS
NOT A POSITIVE, IT'S A NEGATIVE.
IT SPEAKS TO FRANKLY A PANIC
THERE WAS A PANIC IN DECEMBER
AND AN EQUAL AND OPPOSITE PANIC
NOW AS MONEY AGGRESSIVELY TRIES
TO CATCH UP.
AND YET THAT MONEY THAT DROVE US
HIGHER IN JANUARY, FEBRUARY CAN
BECOME AN ACCELERANT ON THE WAY
BACK DOWN AS IT HAS TO REVERSE.
>> YOU'RE DISPUTING THE FACT
THAT YOU THINK THIS IS SIMPLY A
BEAR MARKET BOUNCE
YOU THINK THIS IS A JITTERY
VER --
LEGITIMATE REVERSAL?
>> I THINK WE PUT IN AN EXTREME
DOWNTREND AND AN EXTREME UPTREND
AND CANCELLED THEM OUT
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT THE FED DID.
I REALIZE EARNINGS AREN'T SEXY
AND THE GLOBAL ECONOMY IS NOT IN
GREAT SHAPE.
WE'VE BEEN IN A PLACE WHERE
EQUITIES HAVE PERFORMED IN THAT
ENVIRONMENT.
>>> COMING UP, ENERGY IS DOWN
MORE THAN 2%
ONE OF THE TRADERS THINKS IT'S
ABOUT TO GET A LOT WORSE
HE'LL TELL US HOW HE'S PLAYING
THE CRUDE CRUSH COMING UP.
>>> PLUS GAMING GIANT TAKE TWO
IS HOSTING ITS GAMING LEAGUE
THIS WEEK.
THE CEO WILL BE HERE TO EXPLAIN
WHY HE IS GOING ALL IN ON THE
E-SPORTS FEVER.
>>> CHECK OUT SHARES OF NETFLIX
UNDER PRESSURE AFTER ONE AN LIT
SAYS THE STREAMING COMPETITION
IS HEATING UP.
THERE'S MUCH MORE "FAST" AFTER
THIS
[Leaf Blower]
You should be mad
at leaf blowers.
[beep]
You should be mad your neighbor
always wants to hang out.
And you should be mad your
smart fridge
is unnecessarily complicated.
But you're not mad,
because you have E*TRADE
which isn't complicated.
Their tools make trading
quicker and simpler.
So you can take on the
markets with confidence.
Don't get mad.
Get E*TRADE and
start trading today.
Don't get mad.
I can't believe it.
That there's a lobster
in our hot tub?
Lobster: Oh, you guys.
There's a jet!
Oh...I needed this.
No, I can't believe how
easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
our car insurance with GEICO.
We could have been doing
this a long time ago.
So, you guys staying
at the hotel?
Yeah, we just got married.
Oh ho-ho! Congratulations!
Thank you.
Yeah, I'm afraid of
commitment...
and being boiled alive.
Oh, shoot.
Believe it.
GEICO could save you 15% or more
on car insurance.
That guy's the worst.
This is not a bed...
it's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed, from $999...
senses your movement and
automatically adjusts
on each side to keep
you both comfortable.
And snoring?
How smart is that?
Smarter sleep.
So you can come out swinging,
maintain your inner
focus, and wake up rested
and ready for anything.
Only at a Sleep Number store,
save $500 on select Sleep
Number 360 smart beds.
Plus, free premium
delivery and setup.
Ends March 17th.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "FAST
MONEY.
CHECK OUT SHAERES OF NETFLIX
GETTING HIT TODAY DOWN NEARLY 3%
AFTER A DOWNGRADE FROM BUY TO
NEUTRAL AT BUCKINGHAM RESEARCH
THEY DID KEEP THEIR PRICE TARGET
INTACT BUT THEY'RE LOOKING AT
INCREASED COMPETITION, WHICH I
THINK EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT
STORY.
SUSCEPTIBLE TO JUST A GENERAL
MARKET DOWNTURN.
>> RIGHT
SO RIGHT NOW THEY'RE BASICALLY
RAISING PRICES, LOSING CONTENT,
SPENDING MORE MONEY.
THAT'S THE NEGATIVE STORY,
THAT'S THE HEADWIND.
I DO BELIEVE IF THE OVERALL
MARK, WHICH I THINK IS GOING TO
SELL OFF, NETFLIX HAS TO IN
THEORY SELL OFF.
>> SO YOU AGREE WITH THAT
CRITICAL POINT THAT THEY MAKE.
>> I AGREE WITH THAT PREMISE BUT
LONGER TERM I THINK PEOPLE WILL
HAVE A BUNDLE THEMSELVES OF
STOCK THAT THEY BUY.
THEY'LL BUY THE DISNEY, THEY'LL
BUY THIS ONE AND BUY TWO OR
THREE OTHER ONES
THEY'LL PROBABLY SPENT 40 OR
SOME ODD DOLLARS COLLECTIVELY
WITH ALL THE STREAMINGS THAT
THEY DO BUY.
I THINK THEY'LL HAVE
COMPETITION.
THERE'S ROOM FOR THEM.
BUT YES, I GET THE BEAR STORY ON
NETFLIX.
>> THE TRUTH IS THEY'LL SPEND A
LOT MORE THAN $40.
YOUR BILLS ON THIS WILL LOOK
LIKE YOUR CABLE BILL CIRCA 2009
AND THEN YOU'LL SEE ALL THIS
STUFF REBUNDLED.
HERE'S THE BIG ISSUE WITH
NETFLIX RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN SAY, OH, THAT PRICE
INCREASE WENT REALLY WELL AND
DON'T WORRY.
THEY LOST $3 BILLION IN FREE
CASH FLOW LAST YEAR AND GUIDED
JUST A COUPLE MONTHS AGO TO LOSE
ANOTHER $3 BILLION
AT SOME POINT IF WE ARE GETTING
TO THE END OF A CYCLE ESPECIALLY
WITH ALL THIS COMPETITION, THIS
STOCK WILL NOT BE ABLE TO
LEVITATE.
>> THE STOCK IS BASICALLY FLAT
YEAR OVER YEAR
NOTHING, NOTHING, WITH A LOT OF
VOLATILITY.
>>> COMING UP, THE CEO OF
TAKETWO SAYS E-SPORTS ARE ABOUT
TO GET BIGGER AND BIGGER AND
BETTER THAN EVER
WE'LL TELL YOU WHY HE SAYS WE'RE
NOWHERE CLOSE TO REACHING PEAK
GAMING
WE'RE LIVE FROM TIMES SQUARE IN
NEW YORK CITY TONIGHT.
THERE IS MUCH MORE "FAST MONEY"
RIGHT AFTER THIS
>>> WE'RE PACK ON "FAST MONEY.
GAME ON IS A COMPETITIVE VIDEO
GAME LEAGUE.
IT HAD ITS SECOND DRAFT AT THE
BARCLAY CENTER IN BROOKLYN
74 MEN, 1 WOMAN JOINED TEAMS TO
LIVE A LIFE SOME NOW DREAM OF,
PLAYING VIDEO GAMES
PROFESSIONALLY AS E-SPORTS
ATHLETES
WITH US NOW THE MAN, THE MYTH
AND THE GAMING LEGEND HIMSELF.
TAKETWO CEO STRAUSS ZELNICK.
THAT'S A BIG BUILDUP
BARCLAY CENTER IS HUGE
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE THE GROWTH IN
THESE SPORTS.
>> IT'S GREAT.
IT'S OUR SECOND SEASON
THE FIRST SEASON ENDED WITH A
GREAT RESULT AND EVERYONE IS
LOOKING FORWARD TO THE SECOND
TIP-OFF.
>> WHAT'S THE AVERAGE AGE OF
THOSE WHO COMPETE?
>> THE COMPETITORS ARE ON THE
YOUNG SIDE SO I'D SAY PROBABLY
EARLY TO MID-20s
IN TERMS OF PEOPLE WHO WATCH,
ALL ACROSS THE MAP
MORE THAN 250 MILLION PEOPLE
WORLDWIDE CONSIDER E-SPORTS AN
IMPORTANT FORM OF ENTERTAINMENT.
ABOUT 125 MILLION OF THEM ARE
AVID E-SPORTS WATCHERS.
>> AND SPORTS ARE STILL A BIG
DEAL WITH KIDS PLAYING GAMES, AS
FORTNITE HAS OBVIOUSLY
SKYROCKETED.
MY OWN SON IS STILL PLAYING THE
HOCKEY GAMES, THE BASKETBALL
GAMES AND MADDEN.
>> BASKETBALL, GOOD.
GOOD TO HEAR IT.
>> 2K OBVIOUSLY.
BUT SERIOUSLY, THOSE ARE STILL
POPULAR EVEN IN THE GROWTH OF
THESE OTHER TITLES.
>> WE'RE HAVING A RECORD YEAR
WITH NBA 2K.
ONE OF THE THINGS WE LOVE IS
WHEN THERE ARE MORE HITS IN THE
MARKET, THERE ARE MORE PEOPLE
ENGAGED, THE ENTIRE MARKET
GROWS.
SO WE'RE GOING TO TELL MORE
UNITS THIS YEAR THAN EVER
BEFORE
WE'LL HAVE HIGHER RECURRENT
CONSUMER SPENDING THAN EVER
BEFORE
IT'S A NEW RECORD.
IT'S A TIME SOME OF OUR
COMPETITORS ARE ALSO DOING WELL.
>> TALK ABOUT FORTNITE AND APEX
AND COMPETITION AND WHAT YOU
THINK ABOUT THAT
I'M SURE AS YOU SAID, YOU SEE
THE TRENDS FOR YOU ARE GREAT
>> WE THINK THAT FORTNITE IS A
GREAT THING FOR THE INDUSTRY
IT'S PROBABLY BROUGHT IN A
SOMEWHAT YOUNGER CONSUMER.
I'M OFTEN ASKED IS THAT
SOMETHING THAT'S HURT US
TO THE CONTRARY, NO, WE'VE SEEN
THE MARKET CONTINUE TO GROW.
AT THE SAME TIME FORTNITE HAS
BEEN AN EXTRAORDINARY HIT FOR
EPIC, WE HAD ANOTHER GREAT YEAR
FOR GRAND THEFT AUTO LAST YEAR,
WE HAD A RECORD QUARTER FOR ROCK
STAR GAMES
WE SOLD MORE THAN 23 MILLION
UNITS OF RED DEAD RESEDEMPTION
>> YOU JUST MENTIONED UNITS AND
THAT'S WHAT YOUR TYPICAL
INVESTORS, THEY KIND OF
UNDERSTAND THAT FOR A GAME
MAKER.
HOW ARE YOU MONETIZING THIS NEW
E-SPORTS.
>> THE BIGGEST REVENUE STREAM IS
WHAT WE CALL RECURRENT CONSUMER
SPENDING, WHICH IS EVERY FORM OF
NET BOOKINGS THAT ISN'T A FULL
GAME SALE.
OUR GOAL IS EVERY TIME WE PUT
OUT A TITLE, WE HAVE AN
OPPORTUNITY TO CONTINUE TO
ENGAGE WITH THAT TITLE OVER A
PERIOD OF TIME
IF CONSUMERS DO ENGAGE, THEY CAN
MONETIZE THAT ENGAGEMENT
THAT CAN BE IN-GAME SPENDING,
DOWNLOADABLE ADD-ON CONTENT OR
THE LIKE
THAT'S OUR BIGGEST OPPORTUNITY
AND THAT'S A QUARTER OF OUR
BUSINESS IN THE LAST QUARTER
IN ADDITION, YOU MENTIONED
E-SPORTS AND IT'S TIMELY BECAUSE
WE JUST HAD THE DRAFT.
THAT LOOKS TO BE BREAKING THE
BILLION DOLLAR MARK IN TERMS OF
THE INDUSTRY AS A WHOLE.
REMEMBER, MOST OF THAT STILL
GOES TO LEAGUE OF LEGENDS, WHICH
IS NOT ONE OF OUR TITLES
WE HAVE A COUPLE OF COMPETITORS
WHO ARE DOING WELL
OVERWATCH IS DOING WELL.
NBA 2K IS THE ONE TO WATCH.
>> HOW DO YOU THINK ABOUT ADD-ON
CONTENT WITH YOUR AAA TITLES IN
LIGHT OF FORTNITE?
IS IT THE MICROTRANSACTIONS HOW
YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT ADDING
CONTENT IN
MICROTRANSACTIONS FOUR YOU, IS
THAT THE HIGHEST OPPORTUNITY
>> MICROTRANSACTIONS IS
SPENDING
WHAT WE FOCUS ON IS MAKING THE
HIGHEST QUALITY ENTERTAINMENT
AND ENGAGING OUR CUSTOMER.
IF WE GET THAT RIGHT, MO
MONETIZATION FOLLOWS.
>> TAKETWO, DO YOU WANT TO TRADE
IT TIMMY
>> I'M LONG THE STOCK.
IT'S BEEN A TOUGH RUN.
WE'RE AT A PLACE IN VALUATION,
IT'S COMPELLING RELATIVE TO
ITSELF FOR SURE, BUT TRADING
JUST SOUTH OF 30 TIMES WITH TOP
LINE GROWTH THAT FRANKLY SEEMS
TO BE SOMEWHAT STAGNANT.
I'M A BIG BELIEVER IN THIS
INDUSTRY
I THINK THE VALUATIONS WILL MAKE
SOME OF THESE NAMES START TO
LOOK PRETTY ATTRACTIVE TO MEDIA
COMPANIES.
AS STRAUSS POINTED OUT, THIS IS
AN E-SPORTS WATCHING STORY
GLOBALLY.
>> AND THEY BOTH GOT HIT.
>> ALL OF THEM
ALL OF THEM GOT HIT.
TO TIMMY'S POINT, THIS ONE GOT
HIT THE HARDEST.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A REBOUND
EFFECT OR SOME TYPE OF
REVERSION, I WOULD THINK THAT
THIS IS THE NAME THAT YOU'RE
GOING TO GET IN.
>> HERE'S THE THING.
SO REVENUES ARE STAGNANT, THE
STOCK ALMOST GOT CUT IN HALF IN
THE LAST SIX, SEVEN MONTHS SINCE
THE ALL-TIME HIGHS
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT TRADING AT
3.5 TIMES SALES, THIS LOOKS LIKE
A VALUABLE AND UNDERAPPRECIATED
ASSET BECAUSE IT IS SCARCE
THERE IS ONLY ONE NBA 2K LEAGUE.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT ALL THE
OPPORTUNITIES THAT WILL EMERGE
FROM THIS E-SPORTS PHENOMENON --
>> I'M A GRAND THEFT AUTO GUY.
>> I HAVE NOTICE THAT HE HAD
SOME KIDS WHO GOT ALL IN ON
FORTNITE HAVE GRAVITATED BACK
TOWARDS THE SPORTS GAMES
NOT ONLY MY OWN SON BUT HIM AND
HIS FRIENDS WHERE IT WAS ONLY
FORTNITE AND NOW IT'S BACK TO
THE SPORTS GAMES
MAYBE THEY'RE TRANSTORRE.
>> I THINK ARE CONCERNED ABOUT
THAT.
>> TIME FOR FINAL TRADES
TIM, YOU'RE UP PUT.
>> UNH, GET LONG.
>> UTILITIES, XLU.
>> MR. GRASSO.
>> GE.
>> XLE, SELLG INIT.
>>> OPTIONS ACTION STARTS RIGHT
AFTER THIS BREAK
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.