AND TODAY NANCY PELOSI SAID
TODAY HE'S JUST NOT WORTH IT.
THE GREATER QUESTION IS WHETHER
IMPEACHMENT HAS BECOME A DUTY.
IF THE MAJORITY OF THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES BELIEVES TRUMP
OBSTRUCTED JUSTICE AS I BELIEVE
IT DOES, ISN'T THERE A DUTY TO
ACT?
AS THE WRITER FOR THE NEW YORKER
PUT IT THIS WEEK, IMPEACHMENT
MAY BE TOO GOOD FOR TRUMP.
AND MAY YET PROVE JUST THE THING
FOR THE COUNTRY.
IS IT BETTER TO WAIT FOR SUCH A
CONSTITUTIONAL EXPLOSION OR TO
ACT NOW UPON THE LETHAL
ACCUMULATION OF PUBLIC EVIDENCE
MR. TRUMP HAS ALREADY PILED
HIGH.
THAT IS "HARDBALL" FOR NOW.
"ALL IN WITH CHRIS HAYES" STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
>> TONIGHT ON "ALL IN."
>> DO WE LIKE TUCKER?
>> A FULL-BLOWN SCANDAL AT TRUMP
TV.
>> SHE'S MY FRIEND AND SHE'S
YOUR FRIEND.
JUSTICE JEANNINE.
>> WHY FOX NEWS IS CONDEMNING
ONE OF ITS OWN.
>> IS HER ADHERENCE TO THIS
ISLAMIC DOCTRINE INDICATIVE OF
HER ADHERENCE TO SHARIA LAW.
>> AS THE PRESIDENT KEEPS
LOWERING THE BAR.
>> DOES THE PRESIDENT BELIEVE
THAT DEMOCRATS HATE JEWS.
>> AND THEN DAVE CORN ON NEW
REPORTING ABOUT MAR-A-LARGO AND
THE MASSAGE PARLOR MAGNATE
SELLING ACCESS TO THE PRESIDENT.
>> AND MEDI HASAN.
>> THERE WAS NO MENTION OF THE
TRUMP TOWER MEETING.
>> THEY GOT THE TRANSCRIPT
WRONG.
>> AND SHERROD BROWN DECIDING
NOT TO RUN FOR PRESIDENT.
WHEN "ALL IN" STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING FROM NEW YORK,
I'M CHRIS HAYES, BREAKING NEWS
IN THE SCANDAL THAT IS ENGULFING
FOX NEWS.
MORE AUDIO HAS BEEN UNEARTHED
WHICH WE HAVE HERE EXCLUSIVELY
OF ONE OF THE CHANNEL'S PRIME
TIME HOST USING A HOMOFOEBISM
SLUR AND CALLING THE PEOPLE OF
IRAQ SEMI LITERAL PRIMITIVE
MONKEYS WHO HE HAD ZERO SYMPATHY
BECAUSE THEY DON'T USE TOILET
PAPER OR FORKS.
SOME RACIALLY GROSS THINGS SAID
ABOUT BARACK AND MICHELLE OBAMA
AND THE AUDIO JUST BROKE AND
WE'LL SHOW YOU THAT SHORTLY.
THERE IS NEVER A MEDIA OUTLET
MORE IMPORTANT THAN FOX TO NEWS.
HE WATCHES IT ALL DAY AND LIVE
TWEETS "FOX AND FRIENDS" AND
SOMETIMES ON DELAY BECAUSE HE
DVRs IT AND SENDS ADVERTISEMENTS
FOR IT AND THEY RUN INTERFERENCE
FOR HIM AND IT IS IMPOSSIBLE TO
KNOW WHERE ONE ENDS AND THE
OTHER BEGINS.
LESS THAN A WEEK AGO DISGRACED
EXECUTIVE BILL SHINE WAS THE
WHITE HOUSE COMMUNICATIONS
DIRECTOR BEFORE GETTING TURFED
OUT SO IF THE PRESIDENT SITS
DOWN AT MAR-A-LARGO ON WHAT IS
GOING ON IN THE WORLD, THIS IS
THE THING YOU MIGHT SEE.
>> OMAR WEARS A HIJAB WHICH
ACCORDING TO THE KORAN, 33 COLON
59 TELLS WOMEN TO COVER SO THEY
WON'T GET MOLESTED.
IS HER ADHERENCE TO THIS ISLAMIC
DOCTRINE INDICATIVE TO HER
ADHERENCE TO SHARIA LAW WHICH IS
ANTITHETICAL TO THE UNITED
STATES CONSTITUTION.
>> IS HER RELIGION DEVOTION
ANTITHETICAL TO THE U.S.
CONSTITUTION?
GREAT QUESTION.
THE ON THE FACE BIGOTED COMMENT
IS NOT OUT OF STEP WITH THE REST
OF THE RHETORIC AT FOX NEWS
WHERE ANTI-MUSLIM IS PART OF THE
PROGRAMMING.
THEY SAID WE STRONGLY CONDEMN
JEANINE PIRRO'S COMMENTS ABOUT
ILHAN OMAR AND WE HAVE ADDRESSED
THE MATTER WITH HER DIRECTLY.
SHE SAID SHE DID NOT CALL HER
UNAMERICAN, MY INTENTION WAS TO
ASK A QUESTION AND START A
DEBATE BUT OF COURSE BECAUSE ONE
IS MUSLIM DOESN'T MEAN YOU DON'T
SUPPORT THE CONSTITUTION.
SHE'S JUST ASKING QUESTIONS,
PEOPLE.
JUST PUTTING FORWARD IDEAS TO
DISCUSS LIKE TUCKER CARLSON
DOES.
HE'S ALWAYS JUST ASKING QUESTION
TZ.
NOT DEFENDING ANYTHING, JUST
ASKING QUESTIONS.
>> I'M NOT DEFENDING TRUMP --
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID WHAT HE
SAID ON THE TAPE.
I'M NOT DEFENDING IT.
I'M NOT DEFENDING WHITE
SUPREMACY.
>> YOU DEFEND THE UGLINESS OF A
LOT OF THINGS ONLINE.
I'M NOT DEFENDING THE CREEPINESS
ON THE INTERNET.
I HATE IT LIKE YOU DO.
>> AND EVERYONE KNOWS WHAT
TUCKER IS DOING WHEN HE SAID
THIS INCLUDING WHITE SUPREMACIST
WHO RECENTLY LEAKED CHATS ARE
PRAISING CARLSON FOR HOW HE
INJECTED IDEALS OF WHITE
NATIONALISM TO THE DISCOURSE
THROUGH THIS COWARDLY
DISASSOCIATION WITH HIS OWN
VIEWS BUT CARLSON HAS BEEN DOING
THIS SHSTICK FOREVER.
HE'S MADE ON SHOCK JOCK RADIO
BETWEEN 2006 AND 2011 ABOUT,
AMONG MANY OTHER THINGS, WHEN
CHILD RAPE IS OKAY AND
DEFENSIBLE.
YOU COULD TELL FROM LISTENING
THEY ARE NOT MADE IN JEST.
>> WELL HE -- WARREN JEFFS
DIDN'T MARRY UND AGE GIRLS.
>> HE'S IN PRISON FOR
PRECIPITATION OF CHILD RAPE.
>> WHATEVER THE HELL THAT MEANS.
HE'S IN PRISON BECAUSE HE'S
WEIRD AND UNPOPULAR AND HAS A
DIFFERENT LIFESTYLE THAT PEOPLE
FIND CREEPY.
>> HE'S AN ACCESSORY TO A RAPE
OF CHILDREN AND THAT IS A FELONY
AND A SERIOUS ONE AT THAT.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN AN
ACCESSORY?
HE'S GOT A WEIRD RELIGIOUS CULT
WHERE HE THINKS IT IS OKAY TO
MARY UNDERAGE GIRLS BUT HE
DIDN'T DO IT.
WHY WOULD THE GUY WHO DID IT --
HE SHOULD BE THE ONE DOING LIFE.
I'M NOT DEFENDING UNDERAGE
MARRIAGE.
AT ALL.
I JUST DON'T THINK IT IS THE
SAME THING EXACTLY AS PULLING A
CHILD FROM A BUS STOP AND SEXUAL
ASSAULTING A CHILD.
THE RAPIST MADE A LIFE LONG
COMMITMENT TO TAKE CARE OF THE
PERSON.
LET'S BE HONEST ABOUT.
>> BE HONEST ABOUT THE
DISTINCTION BETWEEN RAPING A
CHILD ONCE AND THEN FORCIBLY
MAINTAINING YOUR CONTROL OVER
THEM TO RAPE THEM AGAIN.
CARLSON WENT TO TWITTER AND DID
NOT APOLOGIZE SAYING MEDIA
MATTERS CAUGHT ME SAYING
SOMETHING ON A RADIO SHOW MORE
THAN A DECADE AGO AND WITH THE
USUAL RITUAL CONTRITION.
THE PRESIDENT OF THE GROUP THAT
UNCOVERED THAT OF MEDIA MATTERS
OF AMERICA AND YOU HAVE NEW
AUDIO YOU JUST PUBLISHED THIS
EVENING.
>> YES.
>> WHERE SHOULD WE START.
THERE IS ONE CLIP IN WHICH HE
USED A HOMOPHOBIC SLUR.
I THINK THAT WE HAVE THAT WHICH
YOU'VE JUST PUBLISHED.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> TUCK, DO YOU LIKE COMING ON
WITH US.
I LIKE YOU.
I'M NOT TRYING TO [ BLEEP ] BUT
>> WELL I LIKE YOU TOO.
AND I MEAN THAT AND YOU SAY THAT
IN A NON -- [ BLEEP ] BY I MEAN
IT IN A [ BLEEP ] WAY.
>> WHAT STRUCK ME ABOUT THE
CLIPS WAS NOT JUST THE FACT THAT
THEY'RE SO CONSISTENT WITH THE
THINGS THAT HE SAYS NOW, BUT THE
COMFORT IN WHICH HE SAYS IT.
IS IT -- IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE
SEEING THE REAL TUCKER CARLSON
AND HOW PRIVATE HE IS AND LIVES
BEHIND A DEEP VENEER AND I FEEL
LIKE THAT'S THE REAL TUCKER AND
THAT STRUCK ME, THE CASUALNESS
TO IT FEELS THAT IS NOT THE ONLY
TIME HE SAID THAT.
>> LET ME JUST SAY, THAT MY
POSITION ON THIS IS LIKE -- THE
MORE INFORMATION THE BETTER AND
PEOPLE SHOULD HEAR AND TUCKER
COULD DEFEND HIMSELF AND OWN THE
THINGS HE SAYS.
LIKE FOR INSTANCE, I HATE THE
WAR -- I'M NOT DEFENDING THE WAR
IN ANY WAY BUT JUST HAVE ZERO
SYMPATHY FOR THEM AS A CULTURE
MEANING IRAQIS WHERE PEOPLE
DON'T USE TOILET PAPER OR FORKS.
THIS IS HIM IN 2008.
THIS IS AFTER HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF IRAQIS HAVE BEEN
KILLED.
IF I DIDN'T LIKE CANADA I
WOULDN'T CONSIDER IT WORTH
INVADING.
I MEAN, IRAQ IS A CRAPPI PLACE
FILLED WITH SEMI LITERAL MONKEYS
AND ISN'T WORTH INNOVATING.
THESE ARE HIS VIEWS AND THEY
SHINE THROUGH.
>> AND THERE WAS A POINT WHERE
HE FACT -- A FANTASIZED ABOUT A
PRESIDENT THAT PROMISED TO RAD
KATE -- ERADICATE MUSLIM.
>> HOW MUCH A CANDIDATE WOULD
CATCH FIRE SAYING I'M SICK OF
P.C. CULTURE, I'M JUST GOING TO
KILL MUSLIMS.
>> AND IF YOU TIE THAT WITH HIS
PROGRAMMING TODAY AND WHY YOU
SEE A WINKING AND NODDING BEFORE
HIS SHOW EVEN LAUNCHED, WE FOUND
HIS NEW PRODUCER GOESING INTO
THE CHAT ROOM AND ANNOUNCING
THEIR THE -- THE PROGRAM WAS
THERE AND INVITING IDEAS AND
THERE IS A SEGMENT THAT IS A TOP
STORY ON THE CHAINS OR ONE OF
THE COMMUNITIES BECAUSE EASEL
VATING IT -- EASEL VATING IT AND
GIVING IT AIR TIME.
>> THIS IS THE DEVIL'S ADVOCATE,
THIS IS SAID 12 OR 13 YEARS AGO
DURING HIS EMPLOYMENT AT THIS
NETWORK, NOT FOX NEWS.
>> CORRECT.
>> AND THIS WAS SAID A LONG TIME
AGO AND YOU'RE DIGGING THIS UP
BECAUSE YOU DON'T LIKE HIM ANY
WAY?
>> THAT IS -- I UNDERSTAND WHY
THAT IS THE CASE.
IF THAT WAS THE CASE, WE JUST
WANTED TO BOMBARD WITH
EVERYTHING, I WOULD HAVE TAKEN
THE HUNDRED PLUS HOURS THAT WE
LISTENED TO AND PLAYED A LOT OF
CLIPS BECAUSE HE SAID A LOT OF
THINGS THAT ARE OBJECTIONABLE.
>> HE SAID STUFF YOU CHOSE NOT
TO PUBLISH.
>> TONS OF IT.
WE DID IT PRECISELY BECAUSE OF
THAT.
I'M NOT BEING A NICE GUY AND
GIVE HIM A FAVOR BECAUSE THE
ARGUMENT FOR PULLING THIS OUT
NOW IS, ONE, BECAUSE OF HIS
RELATIONSHIP TO THE PRESIDENT
AND THE CONSUMPTION, TWO THAT I
THINK IT GIVES CONTEXT ANDIN
SIGHT -- INSIGHT INTO WHAT HE
DOES NIGHTLY ON THE PROGRAM AND
TO THE END THEY ENRICH THAT
UNDERSTANDING IT IS WORTHWHILE
SO WE FOCUS ON THINGS HE SAID
REPEATEDLY AND ECHO HIS
PROGRAMMING TODAY AND THAT MAKES
IT MUCH MORE RELEVANT.
>> THERE IS A RIV ABOUT BARACK
OBAMA -- MICHELLE OBAMA ACTING
LIKE A, QUOTE, SISTER,
EXCESSIVELY BLACK IN THE
ESTIMATION OF THE CO-HOST AND
TUCKER CARL SORN.
>> I THINK HE USED THE
CHARACTERIZATION GHETTO.
>> AND THE IDEA THAT BARACK
OBAMA WOULD STILL BE A STATE
SENATOR IF HE WERE WHITE WHICH
IS ONE THING THAT WAS SAID AT A
CERTAIN POINT.
SO THE RACIAL TY AND RAILING
AGAINST THE CONGRESSIONAL BLACK
CAUCUS AND POLITICAL
CORRECTNESS.
THE CONGRESSIONAL BLACK CAUCUS
EXISTS TO BLAME THE WHITE MAN
FOR EVERYTHING AND EVERYONE
KNOWS IT IS TRUE.
THAT IS THE KIND OF THING SAID
ON HIS PROGRAM.
THIS IS NOT REVEALING ANYTHING
ABOUT THE MAN'S CHARACTER VIEW.
ALL OF THAT COULD BE FOUND AT
MEDIA MATTERS WEBSITE AND LISTEN
TO THE CLIPS AND GET THE FULL
CONTEXT.
AND JOINING ME KARINE
JEAN-PIERRE AND WALEED SHAHID.
WHEN THIS BROKE OVER THE
WEEKEND, THIS IS NOT SURPRISING
STUFF.
ALTHOUGH THE QUOTES ABOUT THE
IRAQIS MAKE ME VISCERALLY
ENRAGED BECAUSE IT IS DISGUSTING
BIGOTRY.
DON JR. SAID I THINK THAT REAL
DONALD TRUMP WAS THE ONE TO PAVE
THE WAY IN RESPONSE TO THE
REFUSAL TO APOLOGIZE, THE ACTS
OF CONTRITION.
HE TALKED IN TERMS JUST BECAUSE
THE MOB WANTS TO TAKE THE LOSS,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
HE SHOWED CONSERVATIVES HOW TO
FIGHT AND WIN.
DO YOU THINK SOMETHING IS
CHANGING IN THE DISCOURSE.
>> NO, WHEN YOU ARE LOOKING AT
FOX -- LET ME ST. PAUL E STEP
BACK.
THERE IS SOMETHING THAT ANGELO
SAID THAT RINGS TRUE TO ME WHICH
IS WHEN YOU LISTEN OR HEAR
TUCKER CARLSON ON THE RADIO
SHOW, IT IS CASUAL.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT HE'S
TOTALLY COMFORTABLE WITH.
WHEN YOU SEE HIM ON TV, SOME
PEOPLE MIGHT SAY IT IS AN ACT.
THAT IS NOT REALLY --
>> IT IS NOT AN ACT.
>> AND NOW YOU KNOW, IT IS NOT
AN ACT.
ANYBODY WHO THOUGHT IT WAS, IT
ISN'T.
HE SAYS THESE THINGS CASUALLY.
AS IF HE'S COMFORTABLE.
THESE ARE HIS VIEWS AND WHAT HE
BELIEVES.
NOW WHEN IT COMES TO FOX NEWS,
THIS IS FOX NEWS.
THEY REPEATEDLY HEAR HOSTS AND
ANALYSTS AND REPORTERS ARE
SAYING THINGS THAT ARE RACIST,
HOMOPHOBIC AND MOSS --
MISOGYNIST AND IT SELLS TO THE
MARKETING TO THE PEOPLE
WATCHING.
>> BECAUSE IT IS PART OF A
POLITICAL PROJECT.
>> RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> THE POLITICAL PROJECT IS WHAT
IS INTERESTING.
OBVIOUSLY HATE CRIMES HAVE GONE
UP FOR THE THIRD TIME THIS YEAR
IN THE COUNTRY AND THE FBI
REPORTED THAT AND ANTI-MUSLIM
SENTIMENT IN THIS COUNTRY IN
2017 IN TERMS OF HATE CRIMES WAS
MATCHED THAT RIGHT AFTER 9/11 SO
THERE IS OBVIOUSLY A -- THIS
DEHUMANIZING RHETORIC DOES
IMPACT MUSLIMS ON A REGULAR
DAILY LIFE AND AS FOR THE
MARRIAGE BETWEEN FOX NEWS AND
THE REPUBLICAN PARTY, IT IS A
COALITION OF WHITE NATIONALISM
AND THE CORPORATE GREED AND IT
MAKES ME SICK THAT THE
FRAUDSTERS AT THE TOP HIGHEST
LEVELS OF FOX NEWS ARE SITTING
AT THE TOP OF AMERICA'S
OLIGARCHY AND PEDALING OUT
CONSPIRACY THEORIES BY MUSLIMS
AND BLACK PEOPLE TO BE THE BLAME
FOR COUNTRY'S PROMISE AND THEY
BELIEVE IT AND MAKING MILLIONS
OF DOLLARS OFF OF THIS.
>> AND I WANT TO BE CLEAR, ONE
OF THE KEY THINGS TO UNDERSTAND
ABOUT THE TRUMP PRESIDENCY IN
THIS MOMENT AND THE REASON THIS
TAPE -- AND I THOUGHT I WAS GLAD
THAT PIRRO SAID WHAT SHE SAID IN
SO FAR AS SHE JUST SAID WHAT IS
THE BELIEF OF MANY PEOPLE AT
THAT NETWORK AND IN THE
CONSERVATIVE MOVEMENT AND IT IS
THAT THIS WOMAN WITH THE HIJAB
IS ANTITHETICAL TO THE
CONSTITUTION.
OWN YOUR VIEWS AND DON'T PRETEND
OTHERWISE.
BUT ONE THING ABOUT YOUR POINT,
ALL OF THAT MASS OTH ANNIE IS
NOT AN ACT.
THEY SIT THERE GETTING THEIR
BRAIN ROTTED BY IT.
>> THAT IS THEIR BELIEF AND TRUE
CORE.
>> AND PIRRO DIDN'T AD LIB.
>> IT WAS LOADED INTO THE
PROMPTER.
>> AND SOMEBODY WROTE THAT FOR
HER AND PROBABLY A PRODUCER
APPROVED THAT LANGUAGE.
LOOK, THIS IS WHAT FOX -- AND
THEY'VE BEEN DOING THIS BEFORE
DONALD TRUMP.
LET'S BE VERY, VERY CLEAR.
ALL OF THE HATRED THEY SPEWED
DURING THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
AND THIS IS JUST WHO THEY ARE.
EVEN RUPERT MURDOCH BACK IN 2015
WAS TWEETING THINGS THAT WERE
ISLAMO PHOBIC AND DISGUSTING AND
THEY PACKAGE THIS AND DO IT 24/7
AND LIES AND HATE AND IT IS
AWFUL AND DISGUSTING.
>> THERE IS A VANGUARD PART OF
IT TOO.
THEY ARE APPEALING TO THE BASE
BUT WE'VE SEEN WITH THE GREEN
NEW DEAL, THIS JUST FULL OF -- A
ASSAULT.
>> AND IT HAS [ INAUDIBLE ].
>> THE DEGREE TO WHICH THE WHITE
HOUSE AND THEY ARE INTERTWINED
IS INDISTINGUISHABLE AND THERE
IS ALSO A USEFUL PROPAGANDA ON
THIS --
>> TRUMP INTRODUCED BILLIONS OF
DOLLARS OF CUTS TO MEDICARE AND
THEY ARE NOT COVERING THAT
BECAUSE THEY WANT TO SEE THE
IDEA OF THROUGH NEW BROWNING
AMERICA AND THE AOC AND THE
ILHAN OMAR OF THE WORLD ARE THE
ONES THAT WANT TO -- AT THE END
OF THE DAY, THIS IS WHERE THE
FOX NEWS EXECUTIVES COME INTO
PLAY BECAUSE AT THE END OF THE
DAY THEY PEDDLING THESE
CONSPIRACY THEORIES BECAUSE THEY
DON'T WANT PEOPLE TO VOTE TO
RAISE TAXES ON THEM TO MAKE SURE
EVERYONE IN THE COUNTRY HAS
HEALTH CARE AND THAT IS WHAT IS
SO SAD AND SICKENING BY FOX
NEWS,ALITY THE END OF THE DAY
THE REASON WE CAN'T HAVE NICE
THINGS IN AMERICA IS BECAUSE OF
THE PEOPLE IN FOX NEWS COLLUDING
TO DESTROY THE SOCIAL FABRIC OF
THE COUNTRY.
>> IF YOU LOOK AT THE POLITICS
OF AUSTRALIA AND ENGLAND AND
U.S. AND THEY ARE A BASKET CASE
WITH THIS RIGHT WING AND THAT IS
WHERE RUPERT MURDOCH MADE HIS
BONES IN ALL THREE PLACES.
>> YOU WOULD SAY IT IS SHAMEFUL
BUT THEY HAVE NO SHAME.
THEY FEEL NO SHAME.
BECAUSE LIKE YOU SAID, IT IS
THEIR CORE.
THIS IS WHAT THEY BELIEVE.
LOOK, AND THERE IS ALSO THIS
BIZARRE RELATIONSHIP.
THE SICK RELATIONSHIP LIKE
DONALD TRUMP NEEDS FOX AND FOX
NEEDS DONALD TRUMP.
AND THE THING ABOUT, TOO, IS
YES, IT IS A PROPAGANDA STATE TV
FOX NEWS AND THE PROBLEM IS
DONALD TRUMP'S ONLY GETTING HIS
INFORMATION FROM FOX NEWS.
>> HE LITERALLY -- THAT IS
LITERALLY HOW THE PRESIDENT
LEARNS ON THE WORLD.
IT IS A CLASSIC EXAMPLE OF THEY
ARE USING WHAT THEY'RE DEALING.
THEY ALL ARE.
THERE IS NO DISTINGUISHING
BETWEEN THE TWO AND THE
PRESIDENT IS A CONSUMER AND AVID
CONSUMER.
HIS VIEW OF THE WORLD AS HE IS
PROUD TO TELL YOU IS FORMED IN
REALTIME BY THE INFORMATION THAT
COMES INTO HIM FROM FOLKS WHO
SAY THAT IRAQIS FOR INSTANCE ARE
SEMI-LITERATE PRIMITIVE MONKEYS.
THIS IS THE BELIEF ABOUT THE
WORLD.
THIS IS THE MAN MAKING --
>> AND TUCKER CARLSON IS GOING
TO BE THIS RISING INTELLECTUAL
STAR OF THE REPUBLICAN PARTY TEN
OR 15 YEARS AGO AND THAT TELLS
YOU WHERE THE REPUBLICAN PARTY
IS IN TERMS OF THEIR IDEAS OF
FREE MARKET ECONOMICS AND SOCIAL
CONSERVATISM, IT IS ALL A SCAM.
>> IT IS NOT AN ACT.
THEY BELIEVE WHAT THEY BELIEVE.
WHICH IS THE IMPORTANT TAKEAWAY
FROM THIS.
KARINE JEAN-PIERRE AND WALEED
SHAHID.
>> AND NEXT THE MASSAGE PARLOR
MAGNATE REPORTEDLY SELLING
ACCESS TO THE PRESIDENT.
WHO IS CINDY YANG AND WHAT IN
THE NAME OF GOD IS HAPPENING AT
THE PRESIDENT'S GOLF RESORT
NEXT.
UNDERSTAND
RESORT
NEXT
UNDERSTAND
I was cured an those
doubts behind.
I faced reminders of my hep C
every day.
But in only 8 weeks
with MAVYRET,
I was cured.
Even hanging with friends
I worried about my hep C.
But in only 8 weeks
with MAVYRET,
I was cured.
MAVYRET is the only 8-week cure
for all common types of hep C.
Before starting MAVYRET
your doctor will test
if you've had hepatitis B
which may flare up
and cause serious liver problems
during and after treatment.
Tell your doctor
if you've had hepatitis B,
a liver or kidney transplant,
other liver problems,
HIV-1, or other
medical conditions,
and all medicines you take
including herbal supplements.
Don't take MAVYRET
with atazanavir
or rifampin, or if you've had
certain liver problems.
Common side effects include
headache and tiredness.
With hep C behind me,
I feel free...
...fearless...
...and there's no looking back,
because I am cured.
Talk to your doctor
about MAVYRET.
.
>>> BY NOW YOU'VE PROBABLY SEEN
PHOTOS OF A CERTAIN REPUBLICAN
DONOR WITH DONALD TRUMP.
HER NAME IS CINDY YANG AND LAST
WEEK THE "MIAMI-HERALD" REPORTED
THAT SHE FOUNDED AND NO LONGER
OWNS THE DAY SPA IN FLORIDA
WHERE THE OWN OF THE NEW ENGLAND
PATRIOTS FOOTBALL TEAM ROBERT
KRAFT WAS ARRESTED FOR
SOLICITING PROSTITUTION.
AND THAT IN A REALLY BIZARRE
TWIST, SHE HAD A TENDING A SUPER
BOWL PARTY THIS YEAR WITH KRAFT
AND DONALD TRUMP AT THE WEST
PALM BEACH COUNTRY CLUB.
YANG FACES NO CHARGES IN
CONNECTION WITH THE KRAFT ARREST
OR THE TRAFFICKING PROBE.
BUT MORE PICTURES OF YANG
SURFACED WITH NOTABLE
REPUBLICANS AND NOW MOTHER JONES
REPORTS THAT YANG MIGHT HAVE
BEEN SELLING ACCESS TO THE
PRESIDENT TO CHINESE EXECUTIVES
AT MAR-A-LARGO.
A REPORTER WHO HELPED BREAK THAT
STORY, DAVID CORN AND MOTHER
JONES JOINS ME NOW.
SHE WASN'T AT THE PARTY WITH
KRAFT HIMSELF, WHO WAS AT THE
SUPER BOWL BUT THERE WITH DONALD
TRUMP.
AND THEN THERE IS ALL OF THE
PHOTOS THAT PROLIFERATE OF HER
WITH EVERYONE IN REPUBLICAN
POLITICS.
WHAT IS YOUR REPORTING SAY ABOUT
WHAT HER LATEST GIG HAS BEEN?
>> WELL, IN ADDITION TO OWNING
CHAIN OF MASSAGE PARLORS, SHE
HAD WHAT SHE CALLED AN
INVESTMENT COMPANY WHICH WAS
GEARED TOWARDS CHINESE CLIENTS.
IT'S MAIN WEBSITE WAS IN CHINESE
AND TALKED ABOUT GIVING ADVICE
TO U.S. BUSINESSES THAT WANT TO
INVEST IN CHINA BUT THE REAL
THING IT SEEMED TO BE DOING WAS
TELLING CHINESE EXECUTIVES THAT
IF YOU COME TO THE UNITED
STATES, I CAN GET YOU INTO TO
SEE PEOPLE IN THE TRUMP CIRCLE.
THE PRESIDENT HIMSELF OR TRUMP'S
FAMILY MEMBERS AND HIS SISTER
ELIZABETH TRUMP GROU AND ELAINE
CHOW.
>> THE TRANSPORTATION SECRETARY
AND WILBUR ROSS AND THE WEBSITE
IS FULL OF PICTURES OF HER
PRESUMABLY CLIENTS HAVING
MEETINGS WITH THESE PEOPLE AND
YOU SAID IN MARA LAGO, BUT IF
EVENTS IN WASHINGTON WITH
CABINET MEMBERS AND IT SAID WE
CAN ARRANGE FOR YOU WHITE HOUSE
DINNERS AND CAPITOL HILL
DINNERS.
IT IS SELLING ACCESS TO THE
CHINESE AND SHE HAS GIVEN OVER
$50,000 -- SHE AND HER FAMILY
MEMBERS TO VARIOUS TRUMP
POLITICAL GROUPS.
SO SHE -- IS SHE PAYING TO GET
ACCESS?
IT SMELLS LIKE PAY TO PLAY.
>> AND THERE IS PICTURES OF ALSO
CLIENTS OF HERS HAVING WHITE
HOUSE MEETINGS AND SUBSTANTIVE
MEETINGS IN THE WHITE HOUSE
ABOUT ISSUES?
>> WELL, WITH MEETING WITH
ELAINE CHOW AND GOING TO AN
EVENT WITH WILBUR ROSS.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED AT
THESE MEETINGS.
WERE THESE MEET AND GREET WHERE
THEY PAID THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS
TO GET A PICTURE, THEY GO BACK
TO CHINA AND SAY, LOOK WHO WE'RE
BUDDIES WITH AND DO BUSINESS
WITH US AND THEN WE REPORTED
YESTERDAY AND I SHOULD SAY I'M
DOING THESE STORIES WITH MY
COLLEAGUES DAN FREEMAN AND DAN
SHOWMAN THAT SHE HAS CONNECTIONS
TO TWO GROUPS LINKED TO THE
CHINESE GOVERNMENT AND THE
COMMUNIST PARTY THERE.
SO THAT RAISES QUESTIONS ABOUT
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE.
>> IS SHE -- PART OF ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT WE'VE LEARNED ABOUT
THE SORT OF SWAMPINESS OF
MAR-A-LARGO, ANYONE COULD KIND
OF HIT UP THE PRESIDENT WITH
THEIR FAVORITE IDEA NEXT TO THE
OMELET BAR AND PLANT A BUG IN
HIS EAR.
WE HAVE THIS CRAZY -- IN TERMS
OF THE EFFICACY OF SELLING
ACCESS TO THIS PRESIDENT IT IS
NOT A CRAZY IDEA AND THERE WAS
AN IDEA ABOUT SOME -- DENTAL
REIMBURSEMENT AND TRUMP IS LIKE,
SEND IT ON TO THE V.A.
LIKE YOU CAN GET PRETTY CLOSE TO
THIS GUY IF YOU PONY UP TO BE IN
THIS CIRCLE OF CRONIES.
>> AND YOU CAN DO IT BY GETTING
A MEMBERSHIP IN THE CLUB.
AND WE DON'T HAVE -- A LOT OF
VETTING OF PEOPLE WHO GO THERE
AND IT SEEMS YOU COULD PAY THIS
WOMAN WHO OWNS THESE MASSAGE
PARLORS AND WHO MAKES DONATIONS
TO -- THE SIZABLE DONATIONS TO
THE REPUBLICAN PARTY AND SHE
SOMEHOW IS ABLE TO EXPLOIT THAT
AND BRING YOU RIGHT INTO
MAR-A-LARGO AND GET YOU A PHOTO
WITH THE TRUMP KIDS, DONALD AND
ERIC AND WITH TRUMP'S SISTER AND
ON THE WEBSITE ITSELF IN
CHINESE, SHE MARKETS, WE CAN GET
YOU IN THERE ON THE NEXT NEW
YEAR'S EVE PARTY AT MAR-A-LARGO,
WE HAVE AN ELITE FORM GOING ON
AT MAR-A-LAGO SO YOU COULD MEET
FAMILY MEMBERS.
IT IS VERY BRAZEN AND NOT SUBTLE
BUT KATE ORRING TO CHINESE.
WE KNOW OF ONE THAT MADE A TRIP
THERE AND HAD A MEETING AND DID
SO THROUGH HER SERVICES.
>> I WANT TO BRING IN CAITLIN
OSTROFF WHO BROKE THE STORY.
WHAT ARE YOU LEARNING ABOUT HOW
THIS WOMAN HAS MANAGED TO BE SO
REMARKABLIOMY -- REMARKABLE
OM NYPRESENT.
>> AND SHE WAS THE FOUNDER TO
THE MASSAGE PARLOR AND THEN
HAVING AN INVESTMENT COMPANY AND
DOING OTHER PRACTICES OUTSIDE OF
BEING A BUSINESS OWNER.
SO THE QUESTION IS, IN A SPAN OF
A COUPLE OF YEARS HOW DID SHE GO
FROM A RELATIVELY SMALL DONOR TO
THE REPUBLICAN PARTY AND TO THE
REPUBLICAN CANDIDATES TO ALL OF
A SUDDEN TAKING SELFIES WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND OTHER
HIGH-RANKING REPUBLICAN
OFFICIALS SO THAT IS NOT
SOMETHING WE COMPLETELY KNOW THE
ANSWER TO.
THERE IS AMBIGUITIES TO HOW SHE
GOT THE CONNECTIONS TO GET THERE
BUT SLEAZE BEEN INCREASINGLY
GIVING MONEY TO CANDIDATES IN
THE LAST YEAR OR SO SO THAT IS
THE QUESTION I THINK US AND
MOTHER JONES AS WELL ARE SEEKING
TO ANSWER, HOW DID SHE GO FROM
THAT ZERO TO 100.
>> FOLLOW UP ON THAT AND I'LL
COME BACK TO YOU, DAVID.
THE "MIAMI-HERALD" SUGGESTS AND
THIS IS NOT THE BIGGEST PART OF
THE STORY, SINCE THE ORIGINAL
WOE FACTORS WHAT SHE FOUNDED THE
SPA THAT BOB KRAFT WAS BUSTED AT
AND AT A SUPER BOWL PARTY
WATCHING THE PARTSZ -- PATRIOTS
AND YOUR REPORTING THAT THEY ARE
OFFERING THE KIND OF SERVICES
THEY'RE OFFERING TODAY.
>> YES.
AND SHE WAS NOT BROUGHT UP ON
ANY CHARGES IN THE ARREST OF
KRAFT.
BUT THERE HAS BEEN PEOPLE WHO
USED TO WORK THERE WHO ALERTED
LOCAL LAW ENFORCEMENT AGENCIES
THAT DID NOT PRESS CHARGES.
BUT THERE HAVE BEEN QUESTIONS
RAISED AS TO WHETHER ILLICIT
ACTIVITIES AND SERVEISES WERE
OFFERED AT HER PARLORS.
A FORMER EMPLOYEE THAT HAD
QUESTIONS ON COMMENTS ON YELP
SAYING THAT THEY HAVE PEOPLE
BEEN SENT THERE AND THEY'VE BEEN
OFFERED SEX OR OTHER
SEXUAL-RELATED SERVICES.
SO THAT IS CERTAINLY WITHIN
QUESTION BUT SHE HASN'T BEEN
BROUGHT UP ON ANY CHARGES
RELATED TO THAT.
>> DAVID, THERE IS PROBABLY SOME
SORT OF -- AT THIS POINT, SOME
PART OF THE INTELLIGENCE
APPARATUS SCRABBLING TO NAIL
DOWN WHAT IS KNOWN ABOUT THIS
INDIVIDUAL GIVEN THE FACT SHE'S
HANGING AROUND MAR-A-LARGO TO
THE PRESIDENT AND SELLING ACCESS
TO HIM.
>> WE GO FROM SEX TO NATIONAL
SECURITY IMPLICATIONS.
IF SHE'S BRINGING IN CHINESE
EXECUTIVES TO MEET PEOPLE IN HIS
CIRCLE AND KNOWN TO THE CHINESE
GOVERNMENT OR AUTHORITIES, YOU
THINK THEY WOULD WANT TO PIGGY
BACK ON THIS.
WE KNOW THERE IS VERY LITTLE
VETTING WHEN THE SESSIONS HAPPEN
AT MAR-A-LARGO AND AS WE
REPORTED YESTERDAY WE KNOW SHE
WORKS WITH TWO GROUPS THAT ARE
OUT THERE PROMOTING CHINA'S TOP
FOREIGN POLICY PRIORITIES.
INCLUDING THE REABSORPTION OF
TAIWAN.
SO THERE A LOT TO DIG INTO HERE.
I HATE TO SAY THIS, CHRIS, BUT
THIS IS ANOTHER CONGRESSIONAL
INVESTIGATION.
THERE ARE SO MANY ALREADY, IT IS
LIKE AIRPLANES ON THE RUNWAY.
YOU CAN'T GET THEM ALL UP INTO
THE AIR BUT IF THIS HAPPENED
UNDER THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION,
YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD BE GOING ON
RIGHT NOW?
>> DAVID CORN, IT IS VERY GOOD.
AND CAITLIN OSTROFF, GREAT
REPORTING.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
>>> JUST AHEAD, A SURPRISE
DECISION IN THE DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL FIELD.
AS SENATOR SHERROD BROWN OF OHIO
ANNOUNCES HE WILL NOT RUN FOR
PRESIDENT.
I'LL ASK HIM WHY HE DECIDED TO
STAY OUT, NEXT.
STAY OUT, NEXT
(indistinguishable muttering)
That was awful.
Why are you so good at this?
Had a coach in high school.
Really helped me up my game.
I had a coach. Math.
Ooh.
So, why don't traders
have coaches?
Who says they don't?
Coach McAdoo!
You know, at TD Ameritrade,
we offer free access
to coaches
and a full education
curriculum-
just to help you
improve your skills.
Boom! Mad skills.
Education to take your
trading to the next level.
Only with TD Ameritrade.
SARAH'S LAST TUITION
PAYMENT, SENT OFF.
FEELING GOOD?
OH YEAH.
NOW I'M READY TO
FOCUS ON MY PROJECT.
♪ ♪ ♪
THIS IS WHY WE PLAN.
YOU NEVER CEASE
TO AMAZE ME, MAYA.
SEE HOW INVESTING WITH A J.P.
MORGAN ADVISOR CAN HELP YOU.
>>> THERE ARE STILL A NUMBER OF
POTENTIAL PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES CONSIDERING ENTERING
THE DEMOCRATIC RACE INCLUDING
JOE BIDEN STILL MULLING OVER HIS
DECISION AND BETO O'ROURKE WHO
WILL HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT SOON
AND TODAY STACEY ABRAMS SAID
THAT A 2020 PRESIDENTIAL RUN IS
ON THE TABLE.
I HEAR THAT AND I WONDER WHAT
THE PERIOD OF CONTEMPLATION
LOOKS LIKE AND HOW SOMEONE MAKES
THE DECISION TO RUN FOR
PRESIDENT.
BECAUSE NOT EVERYBODY DECIDES TO
DO IT LIKE FOR INSTANCE SHERROD
BROWN WHO TOURED THE COUNTRY AND
THEN ANNOUNCED HE WOULD NOT RUN
LAST WEEK.
HOW DID HE MAKE THAT DECISION?
WELL, DEMOCRATIC SENATOR SHERROD
BROWN OF OHIO JOINS ME NOW.
SENATOR, I'M REALLY CURIOUS
ABOUT THIS -- WHAT GOES INTO THE
CALCULATION, BECAUSE YOU
CONSTANTLY HEAR REPORTS ABOUT
PEOPLE, THEY ARE TALKING TO
ADVISERS AND FUNDRAISERS AND
TALKING TO PEOPLE.
WHAT IS IN YOUR HEAD AND WHAT
DID YOU COME TO BELIEVE THROUGH
THE PROCESS THAT LED TO YOUR
DECISION?
>> WELL AS YOU KNOW, CHRIS, I
HAVEN'T HAD A LIFE LONG DREAM TO
BE PRESIDENT.
I'VE KNOWN YOU A LONG TIME AND
YOU'VE NEVER HEARD ME -- NOBODY
THAT I KNOW HAS HEARD ME TALK
ABOUT AS SOMETHING I WANTED TO
DO AT SOME POINT IN MY LIFE AND
THAT BEGAN TO CHANGE IN NOVEMBER
OR DECEMBER WHEN I SAW THAT
JUST -- I JUST THOUGHT DEMOCRATS
WEREN'T TALKING TO WORKERS
ENOUGH AND I DON'T THINK WE WIN
IN THE SOUTH OR THE MOUNTAIN
WEST OR THE MIDWEST IF WE DON'T
TALK TO WORKERS BETTER AND
LISTEN TO WORKERS BETTER AND
WORKERS OF ALL RACES AND I
ANNOUNCED ON THIS SHOW, ON THE
CHRIS HAYES SHOW, A COUPLE OF
MONTHS AGO OUR DIGNITY OF WORK
TOUR AND I UNDERLINE LISTENING
BECAUSE WE SPEND TIME IN EACH OF
THE FOUR EARLY STATES, NEW
HAMPSHIRE, IOWA, AND SOUTH
CAROLINA AND NEVADA LISTENING TO
PEOPLE AND THIS WHOLE IDEA OF
THE DIGNITY OF WORK, WE WANTED
THIS TO BECOME THE NARRATIVE FOR
OTHER CANDIDATES AND I CONSIDER
IT A SELECT IN -- CONSIDER IT A
VICTORY.
IF YOU LOVE FOR YOUR COUNTRY YOU
FIGHT FOR THE PEOPLE THAT MAKE
IT WORK AND I'VE CHOSE TONE DO
THAT IN THE SENATE.
>> BUT WHY?
>> I THINK I COULD HAVE A LOUD
VOICE THERE.
>> AT SOME POINT YOU WERE
CONSIDERING NOT DOING THAT.
THE QUESTION IS DO YOU DRAW UP A
SPREADSHEET OR MAKES A PROS AND
CONS LIST?
WHAT IS THE THING THAT TIPS ONE
OVER WHEN MAKING A MONUMENTAL
DECISION.
>> I THINK IT IS THE QUESTION OF
WHATRY WILLING TO GO THROUGH,
WHAT ARE YOU WILLING TO PUT YOUR
FAMILY THROUGH.
I THINK THAT -- SORT OF THE
JOYFUL WAY I TRY TO DO MY JOB IN
THE SENATE, I DIDN'T FEEL THAT I
COULD DO THE PRESIDENTIAL RACE
QUITE THE SAME WAY AND BE
EFFECTIVE.
AND SO THE DECISION WAS -- I
KNOW EVERYBODY GETS TO IT
DIFFERENTLY.
I THINK IT IS I DON'T LONG TO
HAVE THIS HUGE DESIRE TO BE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
I LOVE MY JOB IN THE SENATE.
I THINK I'M EFFECTIVE AND OUR
DIGNITY OF WORK NARRATIVE
BECAUSE WE STARTED ON THIS SHOW
HAS BECOME A MUCH BIGGER THING
THAN IT WOULD HAVE BEEN.
SO I -- I JUST THINK I'M READY
TO CONTINUE TO DO THIS IN THE
SENATE.
>> WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT THAT, I
WONDER, WAS THERE PRESSURE --
YOU WON THIS RACE -- YOU WERE
JUST RE-ELECTED IN OHIO AND PART
OF THE PEOPLE TALKED ABOUT YOU
AS A POSSIBLE PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATE BECAUSE YOU HAVE THIS
RECORD TO BE A FAIRLY LIBERAL
SENATE IF YOU LOOK AT VOTING
RECORDS IN A CASE THAT HAS
TRENDED CONSERVATIVE AND RED.
AND YOU JUST GOT RE-ELECTED.
YOU CLEARLY HAVE A CONNECTION
WITH THE STATE AND ABLE TO
MESSAGE YOUR POLITICS AND
CONNECT TO VOTERS THERE.
WERE YOU GET ANY PUSHBACK FROM
CHUCK SCHUMER, IF YOU WOULD WIN
THIS THING WE WOULD BE DOWN A
SEAT IN OHIO AND WE WOULD HAVE A
HARD TIME REPLACING BECAUSE THE
GOVERNOR WOULD APPOINT YOUR
SUCCESSOR.
>> NO.
I HEARD THAT FROM SOMEBODY.
I WAS QUESTIONED ABOUT IT BY
MEDIA BUT NOBODY SAID --
INCLUDING PEOPLE IN OHIO AND
SENATE DEMOCRATIC LEADERSHIP,
NOBODY SAID YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
PARTLY BECAUSE WE WOULD BE GLAD
IN THIS TIME TO TRADE A SENATE
SEED FOR THE PRESIDENCY.
AND I THINK THAT THERE IS A
RECOGNITION THAT IF I WERE THE
NOMINEE, I WOULD HAVE PERHAPS
THE BEST CHANCE TO BEAT TRUMP.
BUT I THINK THAT IF THIS DIGNITY
OF WORK THEME -- I WANT
PEOPLE -- I WANT OUR CANDIDATES
TO THINK ABOUT THE GENERAL
ELECTION AND HOW YOU'RE GOING TO
WIN THE GENERAL ELECTION AND IF
THEY START TALKING TO WORKERS,
OF COURSE WE PLAYED A PRO -- A
PROGRESSIVE BASE AND AGAINST
NAFTA AND THE BANKRUPTCY BILL
AND A WHOLE BUNCH OF ISSUES AS A
PROGRESSIVE BUT WE HAVE TO TALK
TO WORKERS.
IF WE DO THAT, I PREDICT WHOEVER
RAISES HIS OR HER HAND ON
JANUARY 20th, 20 -- WHOEVER YEAR
IT WOULD BE, 2021, THEY WILL
TALK ABOUT THE DIGNITY OF WORK
IN HIS OR HER INAUGURAL SPEECH.
>> SHARPEN THAT.
YOU ARE TRYING TO SAY, LOOK,
DEMOCRATS NEED TO BE THINKING
ABOUT A WAY TO TALK TO VOTERS
BROADLY AND APPEAL BROADLY AND
YOU ARE AN EXPERIENCE RUNNING IN
OHIO WHERE THERE IS A BUNCH OF
DIFFERENT CONSTITUENTS AND AS
OPPOSED TO WHAT IS THE THING YOU
ARE WORRIED THE FIELD HAS BEEN
DOING OR IS GOING TO DO THAT
YOU'RE TRYING TO PROVIDE AN
ANTIDOTE TO THAT IS BAD.
>> I DON'T SAY IT IS BAD.
IT MIGHT BECOME THAT.
I DON'T THINK THAT OUR
CANDIDATES ARE THINKING OF THE
GENERAL ELECTION.
I THINK THAT THERE IS A BIT OF
ONE BIRD FLIES OFF THE TELEPHONE
WIRE AND FIVE MORE BIRDS FLY OFF
THE WIRE AND I JUST THINK THERE
IS THAT.
AND I JUST WANT CANDIDATES TO
THINK ABOUT THEMSELVES AND MOVE
THE COUNTRY FORWARD AND THINK
ABOUT THE GENERAL ELECTION, EVEN
THOUGH I HAVE A LIFETIME EFFORT
FROM THE NRA, I GET GUN OWNERS
VOTES IN ZANESVILLE AND
NANCEVILLE AND LYME, OHIO,
BECAUSE I TALK ABOUT KEEPING
HEALTH CARE COSTS DOWN AND GOING
AFTER THE DRUG COMPANIES AND HOW
DO YOU SEND YOUR KID TO
COMMUNITY COLLEGES TO ZANE STATE
OR ROAD STATE AND HOW DO YOU DO
THAT AND IT REALLY IS -- IT
IS -- THIS TOUR WE DID REALLY
WAS A LISTENING TOUR.
I WASN'T TRYING TO GET THE
BIGGEST CROWD.
I WAS LISTENING TO PEOPLE AND
LEARNED STUFF.
ONE WOMAN IN LACONIA, NEW
HAMPSHIRE, SAID YOU HAVE TO RUN
A CHILDCARE FACILITY FOR YEARS,
SAID YOU HAVE TO THINK ABOUT
CHILDCARE A PUBLIC GOOD AND WE
INVEST IN TRANSPORTATION AND
PUBLIC PARKS AND WE NEED TO
INVEST IN CHILDCARE.
AND THE IRONY OF CHILDCARE IS
PEOPLE CAN'T AFFORD IT AND THE
WORKERS THAT PROVIDE CAN'T MAKE
A LIVING WAGE.
SOMETHING IS WRONG THERE.
>> THANK YOU SENATOR SHERROD
BROWN.
A PLEASURE TO HAVE YOU ON.
>>> A WITNESS IN THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION IS CAUGHT IN AN
APPARENT LIE ABOUT A 2016
MEETING IN TRUMP TOWER AND THAT
INTERVIEW AND THE MAN WHO
EXPOSED HIM AHEAD.
PLUS A SPECIAL FORENSIC
INVESTIGATION IN THING ONE AND
THING TWO, NEXT.
STIGATION IN THD
Hi, I'm Bob Harper,
and I recently had
a heart attack.
It changed my life.
But I'm a survivor.
After my heart attack, my
doctor prescribed BRILINTA.
It's for people who have been
hospitalized for a heart attack.
BRILINTA is taken with
a low-dose aspirin.
No more than 100 milligrams
as it affects
how well BRILINTA works.
BRILINTA helps keep platelets
from sticking together
and forming a clot.
In a clinical study,
BRILINTA worked better
than Plavix.
BRILINTA reduced the chance of
having another heart attack...
...or dying from one.
Don't stop taking BRILINTA
without talking to your doctor,
since stopping it too soon
increases your risk
of clots in your stent,
heart attack, stroke,
and even death.
BRILINTA may cause bruising
or bleeding more easily,
or serious,
sometimes fatal bleeding.
Don't take BRILINTA if you have
bleeding, like stomach ulcers,
a history of bleeding in the
brain, or severe liver problems.
Slow heart rhythm
has been reported.
Tell your doctor about bleeding
new or unexpected shortness
of breath
any planned surgery,
and all medicines you take.
If you recently had
a heart attack,
ask your doctor if BRILINTA
is right for you.
My heart is worth BRILINTA.
If you can't afford your
medication,
AstraZeneca may be able to help.
- How many people love you
unconditionally?
WhilIt would mean the worldider
ad     to them,
and they will love you
forever.
>>> THING ONE TONIGHT, THE TIM
APPLE MOMENT JUST WON'T GO AWAY
FOR DONALD TRUMP.
AND THAT IS BECAUSE HE WILL NOT
LET IT GO.
IN CASE YOU'RE OUT OF THE
COUNTRY, LET US REFRESH YOUR
MEMORY ABOUT THE MOMENT WITH TIM
COOK, THE CEO OF APPLE.
>> WE HAVE SO MANY COMPANIES
COMING IN.
PEOPLE LIKE TIM, YOU'RE
EXPANDING ALL OVER AND DOING
THINGS THAT I REALLY WANTED TO
DO RIGHT FROM THE BEGINNING.
I USED TO SAY, TIM, YOU GOT TO
START DOING IT OVER HERE AND YOU
REALLY HAVE.
YOU'VE REALLY PUT A BIG
INVESTMENT IN OUR COUNTRY.
WE APPRECIATE IT VERY MUCH TIM
APPLE.
>> OH, YES, TIM APPLE.
THIS IS THE THING TRUMP HAS BEEN
KNOWN TO DO.
EVERYONE WAS IN HIS -- MAYBE
BECAUSE EVERYONE IN HIS FAMILY
IS NAMED FOR THE COMPANY THEY
WORK FOR.
LAST MARCH HE APPEARED WITH THE
CEO OF LOCKHEED MARTIN MARILYN
HOUSTON.
>> MARILYN LOCKHEED, THE LEADING
WOMAN'S BUSINESS EXECUTIVE IN
THIS COUNTRY ACCORDING TO MANY.
>> HER NAME IS NOT MARILYN
LOCKHEED, SHE DOESN'T HAVE THE
LAST NAME OF THE COMPANY SHE
RUNS, THAT IS NOT THE WAY IT
WORKS.
BUT THE COVERAGE OF TIM APPLE
HAS GOTTEN UNDER TRUMP'S SKIN.
AT MAR-A-LAGO ON FRIDAY NIGHT
WITH NO CAMERAS PRESENT HE
EXPLAINED TO A GROUP OF DONORS
WHAT HAPPENED AND WHAT THEY
DESCRIBED AS ONE OF TRUMP'S
WEIRDEST LIES EVER.
THAT IS THING TWO IN 60 SECONDS.
.
-Driverless cars...
-All ground personnel...
...or trips to Mars.
$4.95.
Delivery drones
or the latest phones.
$4.95.
No matter what you trade,
at Fidelity
it's just $4.95 per online
U.S. equity trade.
.
>>> SO AFTER DONALD TRUMP CALLED
TIM COOK TIM APPLE AND EVERYBODY
HAS A CHUCKLE OVER IT THE
PRESIDENT TOLD A GROUP OF DONORS
AT MAR-A-LAGO THIS WEEKEND, IT
NEVER HAPPENED.
AXIOS REPORTED THAT TRUMP TOLD
THE DONORS THAT HE SAID TIM COOK
APPLE REALLY FAST AND THE COOK
PART OF THE SENTENCE WAS SOFT,
BUT ALL YOU HEARD FROM THE FAKE
NEWS HE SAID WAS TIM APPLE.
WELL, THAT MAKES PERFECT SENSE.
IT IS POSSIBLE THIS LIE WORKED
ON THE AUDIENCE AT TRUMP'S HOUSE
OF FANCY GOLF AND OMELETS, SO
JUST TO BE SURE, THING ONE AND
THING TWO HAS DONE A FORENSIC
ANALYSIS OF THE TAPE.
ENHANCE.
>> WE APPRECIATE IT VERY MUCH
TIM APPLE.
>> YEAH, HE SAID TIM APPLE.
SO THE LIE WAS SO BLATANT THAT
HE CAME UP WITH A NEWS STORY AT
A RECENT ROUND TABLE MEETING OF
BUSINESS EXECUTIVE AND LONG
AFTER FORMALLY INTRODUCING TIM
COOK OF APPLE AND I REFERRED TO
HIM AS TIM APPLE AS AN EASY WAY
TO SAVE TIME IN WORDS.
HOW IS HE STILL WRITING ABOUT
THIS?
WHAT IS -- THIS IS WHY WE
ELECTED HIM.
TO SAVE TIME IN WORDS.
AND NO PRESIDENT HAS EVER SAVED
SO MANY WORDS.
>> YOU KNOW, I'M TOTALLY OFF
SCRIPT.
RIGHT?
>> DARLING IS THE WIND BLOWING
TODAY.
I WOULD LIKE TO WATCH
TELEVISION.
>> HE ASKED RUSSIA TO GO GET THE
E-MAILS.
>> HE'S BAD.
HE'S A BAD, BAD -- HE'S A BAD,
BAD GUY.
>> HEY, DON, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
HOW DONNIE, I LOVE YOU DONNIE.
>> WHITE HAIR?
SEE, I DON'T HAVE WHITE HAIR.
>> RUSSIA, RUSSIA, RUSSIA,
RUSSIA --
RUSSIA,
RUSSIA -
ete job
from any one else.
Why accept it from
your allergy pills?
Flonase Sensimist relieves
all your worst symptoms,
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
And all from a gentle mist
you can barely feel.
Flonase Sensimist.
>>> ONE OF THE STRANGER PLOT
TWISTS IS THE RETURN OF ERIK
PRINCE, THE BROTHER OF BETSY
DeVOS AND FOUNDER OF THE
MERCENARY COMPANY ONCE CALLED
BLACK WATER.
AFTER THE INVOLVEMENT IN
KILLINGS OF IRAQI CIVILIANS
BROUGHT PUBLIC SCRUTINY, PRINCE
REBRANDED THE COMPANY UNDER
DIFFERENT NAMES AND SOLD IT OFF
RELOCATED TO THE UNITED ARAB
EMIRATES AND BEGAN FRONTIER
SERVICES GROUP WHICH MARKETED
SECURITY SERVICES TO FOREIGN
STATES.
THEN IN 2016 HE POPS UP HANGING
AROUND TRUMP WORLD.
DURING THE TRANSITION AFTER
TRUMP WAS ELECTED, PRINCE WAS
PART OF AN EFFORT TO SET UP A
MEETING, MEETING THAT ACTUALLY
HAPPENED WITH THE A RUSSIAN FUND
MANAGER IN THE SEYCHELLES WHICH
HE TESTIFIED ABOUT THE MEETING
WAS UNCLEAR AND THERE WAS A
STRANGE MEETING DURING THE
CAMPAIGN AT TRUMP TOWER THAT
SEEMS TO HAVE BEEN FORGOTTEN
ABOUT.
AS THE "NEW YORK TIMES" REPORTED
THREE MONTHS BEFORE THE
ELECTION, DONALD TRUMP JR. MET
WITH A GULF STATE EMISSARY WHO
WAS OFFERING TO HELP DONALD
TRUMP WIN THE ELECTION.
ERIK PRINCE, THE PRIVATE
SECURITY CONTRACTOR AND FORMER
HEAD OF BLACK WATER ARRANGED THE
MEETING THAT TOOK PLACE AUGUST
3rd, 2016 IN TRUMP TOWER.
APPARENTLY PRINCE DIDN'T TELL
THE HOUSE INTEL COMMITTEE ABOUT
THAT MEETING IN TRUMP TOWER
DURING THE CAMPAIGN AND ASKED
ABOUT HIS OMISSION BY MEHDI
HASAN ON AL JAZEERA SHOW HEAD TO
HEAD.
>> IN NOVEMBER OF 2017 YOU TOLD
CONGRESS UNDER OATH THAT YOU
PLAYED NO OFFICIAL OR UNOFFICIAL
ROLE IN THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN BUT
WHAT YOU DIDN'T TELL THEM IS ON
AUGUST OF 2016 YOU WERE AT TRUMP
TOWER WITH DON JR., AND STEVE
MILLER THEN A CAMPAIGN ADVISER,
GEORGE NADER WHO IS A BACK
CHANNEL TO THE SAUDIS AND
EMIRATES AND A CONVICTED
PEDOPHILE AND JOEL ZEMMEL A
SOCIAL MEDIA EXPERT, HOW COME
YOU DIDN'T MENTION THAT MEETING
TO CONGRESS GIVEN IT IS SO
RELEVANT TO THEIR INVESTIGATION.
>> I DID, AS PART OF THE
INVESTIGATION, I CERTAINLY
DISCLOSED --
>> NOT IN THE
TRUMP TOWER.
THEY SPECIFICALLY ASKED YOU WHAT
CONTACTS YOU HAD AND YOU DIDN'T
ANSWER THAT.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE I WAS ASKED
THAT QUESTION.
>> YOU WERE ASKED ANY
COMMUNICATIONS WITH THE CAMPAIGN
AND YOU SAID APART FROM WRITING
PAPERS AND PUTTING UP YARD
SIGNS, YOU SAID NO.
I HAVE THE TRANSCRIPT TO THE
CONVERSATION HERE.
>> SURE, I MIGHT HAVE BEEN -- I
THINK I WAS AT TRUMP
HEADQUARTERS OR THE CAMPAIGN
HEADQUARTERS.
>> AUGUST 3rd, 2016, USABLE, DON
JUNIOR.
>> WE WERE THERE TO TALK ABOUT
IRAN POLICY.
>> DON'T YOU THINK THAT'S
IMPORTANT TO DISCLOSE.
>> I DID.
>> YOU DIDN'T.
WE JUST WENT THROUGH THE
TESTIMONY.
THERE IS NO MENTION OF THE TRUMP
TOWER IN AUGUST 2016, THERE IS
NOT.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF THEY GOT THE
TRANSCRIPT WRONG.
>> THEY GOT THE TRANSCRIPT
WRONG.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I REMEMBER --
>> THIS IS A PROBLEM FOR YOU
BECAUSE WE KNOW ROBERT MUELLER
HAS GOT A LOT OF GUYS FOR LYING
TO THE AUTHORITIES AND NOT
TELLING THE WHOLE TRUTH.
IS THAT A PROBLEM NOW IF YOU
ACCIDENTLY DIDN'T TELL THEM THAT
COULD COME BACK AND HAUNT YOU?
>> I FULLY COOPERATED AND
HAVEN'T HEARD FROM ANYBODY IN
MORE THAN NINE MONTHS.
>> HOUSE INTEL CHAIR ADAM SCHIFF
RESPONDS TO THAT AND I'LL TALK
WITH HASSAN HIMSELF AFTER THE
BREAK.
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
MSELF AFTER T
BREAK.
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
They're America's
biopharmaceutical researchers.
Pursuing life-changing cures
in a country that fosters
innovation
Here, they find breakthroughs...
Like a way to fight cancer
by arming a patient's own
T-cells...
Because it's not just about
the next breakthrough...
It's all the ones after that.
Flight number 417 is being...
You should be mad at airports.
Excuse me,
where is gate 87?
You should be mad at
non-seasoned travelers.
And they took
my toothpaste away.
And you should be mad at people
who take unnecessary risks.
How dare you, he's my
emotional support snake.
But you're not mad,
because you have E*TRADE,
whose tech helps you understand
the risk and reward potential
on an options trade
It's a paste. It's not
liquid or a gel.
and even explore what-if
scenarios.
Where's gate 87?
Don't get mad.
I have a vision
correction number,
But I'm more than a number.
When I'm not teaching,
I'm taking steep grades
and tight corners.
My Essilor lenses offer more
than vision correction
with three innovative
technologies
For my ultimate in vision
Clarity
And Protection
Together in a single lens:
The Essilor Ultimate
Lens Package.
So, I can do more
of what I love!
Buy two pairs of
Essilor's best lenses
and get a $100 back instantly.
See more. Do more. Essilor
>>> I THINK I WAS AT TRUMP
HEADQUARTERS OR THE CAMPAIGN
HEADQUARTERS.
>> TRUMP TOWER, AUGUST 3rd,
2016.
>> YOU, AN ISRAELI DUDE, BACK
CHANNEL TO THE SAUDIS, DONE
JUNIOR.
>> THERE TO TALK ABOUT IRAN
POLICY.
>> YOU WERE THERE TO TALK ABOUT
IRAN POLICY?
>> UH-HUH.
>> ISN'T THAT IMPORTANT TO
DISCLOSE UNDER OATH?
>> I DID.
>> THERE IS NO MENTION OF THE
TRUMP TOWER MEETING 2016.
WHY NOT?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF THEY GOT THE
TRANSCRIPT WRONG.
>> ERIK PRINCE IS SUGGESTING HE
DIDN'T LIE TO CONGRESS AND ADAM
SCHIFF SIGNIFICANT --
SUGGEST
OTHERWISE.
>> BOB MUELLER HAS THAT
TESTIMONY ALREADY.
AND BOB MUELLER WILL HAVE TO
MAKE THE DECISION ABOUT WHETHER
THAT RISES TO THE LEVEL OF
DELIBERATE FALSEHOOD.
>> JOINING ME IS MEHDI HASAN.
GOOD INTERVIEW.
GETTING LOTS OF KUDOS, VERY RARE
TO FIND SOMEONE THAT CAUGHT AS
ERIK PRINCE WAS.
HOW DID YOU NOTICE THAT
OMISSION?
>> I HAVE A GREAT TEAM OF
PRODUCERS AND RESEARCHERS WHO
WENT THROUGH EVERY SINGLE PAGE
OF THAT.
I WISH I COULD SAY I WENT
THROUGH EVERY PAGE OF THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
TESTIMONY, BUT, YOU KNOW, IT'S
SOMETHING WE WANTED TO TALK TO
HIM ABOUT.
HE HADN'T BEEN PRESSED ABOUT HIS
ROLE IN THE MEETINGS BOTH IN THE
SEYCHELLES.
WE WANTED TO GET HIM IN THE
RECORD TALKING PUBLICLY ABOUT IT
BECAUSE HE'S NOT COMFORTABLE
TALKING ABOUT IT.
YOU SAW HIS BODY LANGUAGE.
WHAT IS ABSURD HE HAD ALL OF
THIS TIME TO THINK ABOUT A
DEFENSE AND CAME UP WITH THEY
GOT THE TRANSCRIPT WRONG.
COME ON.
>> WHAT'S ALSO STRIKING IS JUST
HOW WEIRD THIS MEETING IS.
SIT BACK FOR A SECOND.
THAT'S WHAT I WAS REALLY GLAD --
IT'S AUGUST.
TRUMP IS A NOMINEE.
YOU'RE MEETING WITH THE
CANDIDATE'S SON AT TRUMP TOWER
WITH THIS VERY SKETCHY DUDE
GEORGE NATER WHO IS A BECOME
CHANNEL AND BEEN CONVICTED OF
CHILD MOLESTATION WITH THIS
ISRAELI SORT OF SOCIAL MEDIA
GURU DUDE.
WHAT DO WE KNOW WHAT THAT
MEETING WAS ALL ABOUT?
>> WHAT IS INTERESTING IS I
DIDN'T GET AROUND TO ASKING HIM.
HE VOLUNTEERED THAT IT WAS ABOUT
IRAN POLICY THINKING THAT THAT
WOULD BE SOME SORT OF GOOD
ANSWER.
THAT MAKES EVERYTHING MUCH WORSE
FOR HIM BECAUSE THAT'S A PRETTY
CONSEQUENTIAL ISSUE.
WHY IS STEVEN MILLER ASK DONALD
TRUMP JUNIOR WERE EXPERTS ON THE
MIDDLE EAST NATIONAL SECUITY
HAVING A PRIVATE MEETING WITH
THE SAUDI GOVERNMENTS, GEORGE
NATR AND THIS EXPERT THAT RUNS
THIS IF I RECALL AND ERIK PRINCE
A FORMER COMPANY GUY.
IT'S A WEIRD GROUP OF PEOPLE
TALKING ABOUT IRAN AND WE KNOW
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IS
VERY, VERY HAWKISH ON IRAN.
WE KNOW THE SAUDIS HAVE WANTED A
CONFLICT WITH IRAN FOR A LONG
TIME AND HERE IS WHAT IS
INTERESTING, WE TALK ABOUT
COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA AS IF THAT
WAS THE ONLY FOREIGN GOVERNMENT
THAT WANTED TO SEE TRUMP ELECTED
AND GOT INVOLVED.
WE NOW THE GULF COUNTIES LIKE
SAUDI ARABIA AND NETANYAHU WERE
KEEN TO SEE A DONALD TRUMP
PRESIDENT.
THAT'S WHY THE MUELLER INVEST
-- INVESTIGATION IS
INTERESTING.
THIS MEETING IS A CLASSIC
EXAMPLE OF THAT.
WHY IS AN COMING TO THE TRUMP
TOWER.
NATR BROUGHT A PLAN USING
PRIVATE CONTRACTORS, WHICH IS
PRINCE'S SPECIAL.
>> THERE IS A NEXUS.
YOU HAVE THIS MEETING AND AFTER
THE TRANSITION YOU HAVE A NEXUS
BECAUSE HE IS INVOLVED IN THIS
CRAZY MEETING SET UP IN THE
SEYCHELLES THAT HAS THE SECURITY
DUDE FOR THE RUSSIAN HEDGE FUND
GUY.
>> HE'S NOT JUST A HEDGE FUND
GUY BUT THE HEAD OF THE RUSSIAN
DIRECT INVESTMENT AUTHORITY VERY
CLOSE TO PUTIN AND LEAKED
E-MAILS REFERRED AS THE
MESSENGER TO PRESIDENT PUTIN AND
I ASK ERIK PRINCE WHY DID YOU GO
TO THIS MEETING IN THE
SEYCHELLES?
HE SAID IT WAS AN ACCIDENT, I
HAD A BEER WITH HIM.
YOU FLEW HALF WAY AROUND THE
WORLD WITH A CLOSE ALLY OF
VLADIMIR PUTIN TO DRINK A BEER?
REALLY?
COME ON.
THESE LIES ARE ABSURD.
>> THERE ARE MANY INDICATIONS
THAT MEETING, SO THERE IS THE
AUGUST 3rd MEETING.
>> NINE DAYS BEFORE THE
INAUGU
INAUGURATION.
>> THE GEORGE NATER FIGURE.
>> AND A CONVICTED PEDOPHILE.
REMEMBER, TRUMP SURROUNDS
HIMSELF WITH THE BEST PEOPLE.
>> GEORGE NATER, ERIK PRINCE,
THE SEYCHELLES MEETING.
THERE IS LOTS OF EVIDENCE
FOREIGN INFLUENCE WASN'T
ROOTING, THERE IS A WEIRD TRY
ANGULATION WHO ARE ALL WORKING
VARIOUS DIFFERENT ANGLES.
>> YES, FLYNN AND KUSHNER MEET
WITH KISLYAK AND FLYNN WANTS TO
GO TO THE SEYCHELLES OR WHEREVER
IT IS AND HE'S TOLD YOU'RE TOO
HIGH PROFILE.
THAT'S WHY PRINCE IS SEEN AS THE
BACK CHANNEL.
PRINCE DENIES THIS AND SAYS I
WENT FOR THE BEER BECAUSE YOU