FORMS INCLUDING TAX BREAK.
WE'LL SEE OTHER CANDIDATES GIVE
THEIR IDEA WHETHER THEY SUPPORT
IT OR NOT.
>> FURTHER ON THE DECLARATION OF
EMERGENCIES.
A LOT OF CONSERVATIVE SENATORS
ARE GOING TO VOTE AGAINST IT.
THEY LIKE THE FUNDING OF THE
WALL BUT THEY DON'T LIKE THE
ABUSE OF PRESIDENTIAL POWER.
>> I WOULD SAY THE PRESIDENT'S
BUDGET AS WE ARE SPEAKING, NANCY
PELOSI, PUT OUT A RELEASE, BRING
OUT THE WALL, WE'LL NOT GIVE IT
TO YOU.
>> I, TOO, WILL BE COVERING THE
DECLARATION.
>> THAT'LL BE IT FOR US TONIGHT,
COMING UP NEXT, "RUSSIA IF YOU
ARE LISTENING," AN MSNBC'S
SPECIAL FROM ALI VELSHI.
>> THIS IS AN MSNBC SPECIAL
PRESENTATION.
>>> ALL WE HEAR ABOUT IS THIS
PHONY RUSSIA WITCH HUNT.
>> THE MUELLER/RUSSIA REPORT IS
NOT READY YET.
>> WASHINGTON IS IN EAGER AND
ANTICIPATION MODE.
OUR REPORT IS.
>> THIS IS REALLY IMPORTANT.
THE UNPRECEDENTED MOMENTS.
>> THOSE WERE LIES AND I AM SO
SORRY THAT THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
WERE TOLD THAT.
>> MR. TRUMP KNEW OF AND
DIRECTED THE TRUMP MOSCOW
NEGOTIATIONS THROUGHOUT THE
CAMPAIGN AND LIED ABOUT IT.
>> THE INFAMOUS MEETING.
>> WHEN YOU TELL SOMEONE YOU
HAVE DIRT, ONCE YOU GET A YES,
YOU HAVE HOOKED YOUR FISH.
BECAUSE THEY LIED THAT MAKES IT
LOOK MORE SIGNIFICANT THAN IT
IS.
>> THE AGGRESSIVE DEFENSE.
>> FAKE NEWS OF THE RUSSIA WITCH
HUNT.
>> TRUMP CREATE A GREAT JOB
CREATING AN ATMOSPHERE THAT A
THIRD OF THE COUNTRY WILL NOT
BELIEVE ANYTHING THAT ROBERT
MUELLER SAYS.
>> HOW DO WE GET HERE?
>> I AM CONCERNED THAT DONALD
TRUMP IS BEHAVING SOMEONE WHO
MAY HAVE BEEN COMPROMISED OR
BLACKMAILED BY RUSSIA.
>> THE HOUSE COMMITTEE SENDING
OUTLETERS TO INDIVIDUALS LOOKING
FOR THESE THINGS.
>> IT IS HARD TO IMAGINE THE
WORSE THING THAT HAPPENS TO
DONALD TRUMP WAS BEING ELECTED
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES.
>> RUSSIA, IF YOU ARE LISTENING,
I HOPE YOU ARE ABLE TO FIND THE
30,000 E-MAILS THAT ARE MISSING.
>>> FOR MORE THAN TWO YEARS, THE
NATION HAS BEEN CONSUMED BY
QUESTIONS ABOUT WHETHER TRUMP
CAMPAIGN AND THE RUSSIANS
INTERFERED IN THE 2016
ELECTIONS?
>> WE HAVE A SPECIAL COUNSEL TO
HEAD THE RUSSIA INVESTIGATION.
>> THE FBI RAIDED THE OFFICE OF
THE LAWYER OF THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES.
>> THERE IS STILL NO EVIDENCE OF
COLLUSION BETWEEN THE PRESIDENT
AND ANYONE.
>> WAS THERE COLLUSION,
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE, IMPROPER
CONTACT BETWEEN RUSSIAN
OFFICIALS AND THE CAMPAIGN?
IT IS THE FOCUS OF THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION AND WHAT WE'LL
DIVE INTO TONIGHT.
BEGINNING WITH THE QUESTION, HOW
DID WE GET HERE?
>> WE NEED MORE LOVE AND
KINDNESS IN THIS COUNTRY.
JUST DAYS BEFORE DEMOCRATS WOULD
NAME HILLARY CLINTON THEIR
PRESIDENTIAL NOMINEE, WIKILEAKS
UPLOADED NEARLY 20,000 HACKED
E-MAILS.
>> U.S. INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES
BELIEVE RUSSIAN CYBER SPIES
HACKED INTO THE COMPUTER
BELONGING TO THE DEMOCRATIC
NATIONAL COMMITTEE.
>> THEY REALIZED WHAT THEY HAD
BEEN LOOKING AT IS A CREDIBLY
COMPLEX TACT DIRECTED BY THE
KREMLIN DESIGNED UNDERMINE OUR
DEMOCRACY, DEFEAT HILLARY
CLINTON AND ELECT DONALD TRUMP.
>> WHICH AS ESPECIALLY IN
HINDSIGHT MADE THAT NOW FAMOUS
PRESS CONFERENCE EVEN MORE
UNFORGETTABLE.
>> RUSSIA, IF YOU ARE LISTENING,
I HOPE YOU ARE ABLE TO FIND THE
30,000 E-MAILS THAT ARE MISSING.
>> APPARENTLY, RUSSIA WAS
LISTENING.
>> THE RUSSIANS TOOK IT.
WITHIN HOURS THEY STARTED TRYING
TO HACK HER SERVER.
FORMER TRUMP CAMPAIGN ADVISER,
SAM NUNBERG.
>> IT IS NOT A COINCIDENCE.
RUSSIA TOOK IT LITERALLY.
>> DAYS AFTER TRUMP'S UNUSUAL
REQUEST, THE FBI OPENED A
COUNTER INTELLIGENCE INTO
RUSSIA'S ATTEMPT TO INFLUENCE
THE ELECTION AND ANY POSSIBLE
CONNECTION WITH THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN.
>> THEY SAID YOU ADMIRE
PRESIDENT PUTIN?
>> I SAID I DON'T ADMIRE HIM, I
SAID HE'S A STRONG LEADER, MAY
BE BAD OR GOOD.
>> TRUMP'S REGARD FOR VLADIMIR
PUTIN ALSO PEAKED THE INTEREST
OF THE FBI AS DID THE MANY
RUSSIA CONNECTIONS AMONG HIS
CAMPAIGN STAFFS.
>> YOU HAVE CARTER PAGE AND
GEORGE PAPADOPOULOS AND FELIX
SATER, ALL OF THESE CHARACTERS
WERE HAVING CONTACTS WITH
RUSSIAN OFFICIALS IN ONE WAY OR
ANOTHER.
>> MICHAEL FLYNN, THE ADVISER
WITH A RUSSIAN CONNECTION,
MICHAEL FLYNN.
>> WE DO NOT NEED A RECKLESS
PRESIDENT WHO BELIEVES SHE IS
ABOVE THE LAW.
>> IN 2015, FLYNN HAD TRAVELED
TO MOSCOW WHERE HE WAS PAID TO
APPEAR ON R.T., RUSSIA TODAY.
>> I KNOW HE SAID THAT AND I
DISAGREE WITH THAT.
I DEFINITELY DISAGREE WITH THAT.
>> HE STOOD AND APPLAUDED
PUTIN'S SPEECH WHEN EMERGED
LATER THAT HE WAS PAID, HIS
COMPANY WAS PAID SOME $45,000.
>> AFTER TRUMP'S VICTORY IN
NOVEMBER, HE NAMED FLYNN
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER
AGAINST THE ADVICE OF OUT GOING
PRESIDENT BARACK OBAMA WHO
REPORTEDLY WARNED TRUMP THAT
FLYNN LACKED THE TEMPERAMENT FOR
THE JOB.
>> I HAD THE OPPORTUNITY TO HAVE
THE CONVERSATION WITH
PRESIDENT-ELECT TRUMP, PRESIDENT
OBAMA STRUCK BACK AT RUSSIA FOR
THE CYBER ATTACK EJECTING 35
SUSPECTED RUSSIAN SPIES FROM THE
U.S. AND IMPOING SANCTIONS
AGAINST RUSSIAN INTELLIGENCE
SERVICES.
>> VLADIMIR PUTIN RESPONDED
SURPRISINGLY BY NOT RESPONDING.
>> HE ANNOUNCED HE WOULD NOT
RETALIATE AGAINST THE U.S. FOR
POSING NEW SANCTIONS TO
INTERFERE WITH THE ELECTION.
>> WHAT THE PUBLIC DID NOT KNOW
WAS ON THE DAY PRESIDENT OBAMA
ANNOUNCED THOSE SANCTIONS,
MICHAEL FLYNN, HAD CONVERSATIONS
WITH SERGEI KISLYAK.
>> ONE OF THE THINGS HE SAID WAS
BASICALLY DON'T REACT TO THIS.
HOLD TIGHT, THERE IS A NEW
ADMINISTRATION COMING IN AND IT
WON'T BE A PROBLEM.
>> GENERAL FLYNN SHOULD HAVE
KNOWN THE FBI MONITORS ALL CALLS
WITH FOREIGN DIPLOMATS TO U.S.
CITIZENS.
>> THE DUTIES OF THE OFFICE ON
WHICH I AM ABOUT TO ENTER.
>> SOON AFTER FLYNN WAS SWORN IN
AS NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER,
SHE WAS QUESTIONED BY THE FBI.
>> HE WAS ASKED ABOUT HIS
CONTACTS WITH THE RUSSIANS
DURING THE PRESIDENTIAL
TRANSITION.
>> HE DENIED THAT HE DISCUSSED
THE SANCTIONS WHEN REALLY THEY
HAD EVIDENCE THAT HE HAD IN FACT
BROUGHT IT UP.
>> U.S. INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS
BELIEVE FLYNN MADE THE SAME
DENIAL TO VICE PRESIDENT-ELECT
PENCE.
OVER AT THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT,
TOP OFFICIALS KNEW FLYNN HAD
BEEN UNTRUTH.
DEPUTY ATTORNEY GENERAL
SALLY YATES SHARED HER CONCERNS.
>> SHE THOUGHT FLYNN WAS
BLACKMAILED BECAUSE HE DID NOT
TELL THE TRUTH.
>> I HAD TO STATE THE OBVIOUS,
YOU DON'T WANT YOUR NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISER COMPROMISE WITH
THE RUSSIANS.
>> THE PRESIDENT IGNORED THE
WARNINGS AND THE NEXT 18 DAYS
DID NOTHING TO CORRECT THE
PUBLIC DECEPTION.
>> HE'S TRYING TO HOLD ONTO
MICHAEL FLYNN DESPITE THE FACT
THAT HE'S COMPROMISED.
FOR PROSECUTORS, IT RAISES ONE
QUESTION, WHY?
>> THE WASHINGTON POST JUST
POSTED THIS NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISER, MICHAEL FLYNN,
DISCUSSED SANCTIONS BEFORE TRUMP
TOOK OFFICE DESPITE DENIALS,
OFFICIALS SAY.
>> NOT UNTIL THE WASHINGTON POST
REVEALED FLYNN HAD DISCUSSED
SANCTIONS WITH RUSSIA.
>> NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER,
MICHAEL FLYNN HAS RESIGNED.
>> A DAY AFTER HE RESIGNED, THE
PRESIDENT MET WITH THE MAN
OVERSEEING THE FBI
INVESTIGATION, DIRECTOR JAMES
COMEY.
>> COMEY IS AT THE WHITE HOUSE
FOR A MEETING AND TRUMP KICKS
EVERYONE OUT IN THE ROOM AND HE
WANTS TO TALK ABOUT THE FLYNN
INVESTIGATION.
LOOK, FLYNN DID NOT DO ANYTHING
WRONG, I NEED YOU TO MOVE PASS
AND NOT DO THIS INVESTIGATION.
COMEY WAS ASKED ABOUT THE
CONVERSATION AT A CONGRESSIONAL
HEARING.
>> HE'S A GOOD GUY.
I HOPE YOU CAN LET THIS GO.
NOW, THOSE ARE HIS EXACT WORDS,
CORRECT?
>> YES.
>> HE DID NOT ORDER YOU TO LET
IT GO.
>> I TOOK IT AS A DIRECTION.
IT IS A PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES WITH ME ALONE SAYING I
HOPE THIS, I TOOK IT AS THIS IS
WHAT HE WANTS ME TO DO.
I DID NOT OBEY THAT BUT THAT'S
WHAT I TOOK IT.
>> THE PRESIDENT DENIED ASKING
COMEY TO STOP INVESTIGATING
FLYNN.
A LITTLE MONTH LATER, HE TOOK
THE SHOCKING STEP OF DISMISSING
THE FBI DIRECTOR.
>> COMEY IS OUT IN LOS ANGELES,
TALKING TO SOME STAFF THERE AND
HE LOOKS UP AND SEES ON THE
TELEVISION IN THE BACK OF THE
ROOM, THE CRAWL, THE BREAKING
NEWS ALERT THAT HE'S BEEN FIRED.
HE SAYS -- THAT'S FUNNY, HIS
AIDES COME UP TO HIM AND SAY,
ACTUALLY SIR, THIS IS NOT A
JOKE.
TRUMP APPEARED CRYSTAL CLEAR
ABOUT IT THE NEXT DAY.
>> THE PRESIDENT WAS IN THE OVAL
OFFICE WITH THE RUSSIAN
AMBASSADOR, SERGEI KISLYAK AND
LAVROV AND ACCORDING TO PRESS
ACCOUNTS OF THAT MEETING, HE
DESCRIBED JAMES COMEY AS A "NUT
JOB" AND BOASTED THAT HE HAD
RELIEVED A LOT OF PRESSURE ON
HIMSELF BY GETTING RID OF HIM.
TRUMP ECHOED A SIMILAR SENTENCE
INTO NBC NEWS ANCHOR, LESTER
HOLT.
>> MONDAY YOU MET WITH ROD
ROSENSTEIN, DID YOU ASK HIM FOR
A RECOMMENDATION?
>> REGARDLESS OF RECOMMENDATION,
I WAS GOING TO FIRE COMEY
KNOWING THERE IS NO GOOD TIME TO
DO IT.
IN FACT, WHEN I DECIDED TO DO
IT, I SAID TO MYSELF, YOU
KNOW -- THIS RUSSIA THING WITH
TRUMP AND RUSSIA IS A MADE-UP
STORY, IT IS AN EXCUSE BY THE
DEMOCRATS FOR HAVING LOST IN THE
ELECTION.
>> A WEEK LATER, DEPUTY ATTORNEY
GENERAL, ROD ROSENSTEIN,
ANNOUNCED HE WAS APPOINTING A
SPECIAL COUNSEL TO OVERSEE THE
RUSSIA INVESTIGATION.
IT WAS A TURNING POINT IN THE
TRUMP PRESIDENCY THAT DONALD
TRUMP BLAMED ON ATTORNEY GENERAL
JEFF SESSIONS.
A TOP ADVISER DURING THIS
CAMPAIGN.
>> I HAD INVOLVEMENT WITH THE
CAMPAIGN, I SHOULD NOT BE
INVOLVED IN ANY CAMPAIGN
INVESTIGATIONS.
THEREFORE, I HAVE RECUSED MYSELF
IN THE MATTERS THAT DEAL WITH
THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN.
>> HIS RECUSAL GAVE ROD
ROSENSTEIN THE POWER TO APPOINT
A SPECIAL COUNSEL, HIS CHOICE,
ROBERT SWAN MUELLER III.
>> COMING UP, I AM VERY
CONCERNED THAT DONALD TRUMP IS
BEHAVING LIKE SOMEONE WHO MAY
HAVE BEEN COMPROMISED OR
BLACKMAILED BY RUSSIA.
I'm 3,000,
I'm connected with my boys.
Just pull on over,
see my son's game,
and I'm having a ball.
(VO)
There when it matters.
Buy the new Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e on us.
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it from
your allergy pills?
Flonase Sensimist relieves
all your worst symptoms,
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
And all from a gentle mist
you can barely feel.
Flonase Sensimist.
IF YOU HAVE A GARDEN YOU KNOW,
WEEDS ARE LOWDOWN
LITTLE SCOUNDRELS.
DON'T STOOP TO THEIR LEVEL.
DRAW THE LINE WITH THE
ROUNDUP SURE SHOT WAND.
IT EXTENDS WITH A
PROTECTIVE SHIELD
AND TARGETS WEEDS
MORE PRECISELY.
IT LETS YOU KILL WHAT'S BAD
RIGHT DOWN TO THE ROOT
WHILE GUARDING THE GOOD.
ROUNDUP SURE SHOT WAND.
AND TO STOP WEEDS
BEFORE THEY START,
ALSO TRY ROUNDUP
LANDSCAPE WEED PREVENTER.
ROUNDUP BRAND.
TRUSTED FOR OVER 40 YEARS.
Let's see, ALEVE is
proven better on pain
than Tylenol Extra Strength.
And last longer
with fewer pills.
So why am I still
thinking about this?
I'll take Aleve.
ALEVE.
Proven better on pain.
>>> DONALD TRUMP RAN FOR
PRESIDENT CLAIMING HE MASTERED
THE ART OF THE DEAL.
>> IN 2016, DID VLADIMIR PUTIN
MAKE HIM AN OFFER HE COULD NOT
REFUSE?
LIKE PRESIDENT TRUMP, VLADIMIR
PUTIN, HAS SUPREME POLITICAL
POWER AND INCREDIBLE PERSONAL
WEALTH.
IN 2012, U.S. SANCTIONS, MADE
PUTIN A FORTUNE INTO ACHILLES'
HEELS.
>> VLADIMIR PUTIN DOES NOT KEEP
MONEY IN HIS OWN NAME.
HE KEEPS MONEY IN THE NAMES OF
MANY RUSSIAN OLIGARCHS.
THIS WILL FREEZE THE ASSETS.
I BELIEVE THAT PUTIN IS THE
RICHEST MAN IN THE WORLD.
I BELIEVE HE'S WORTH
$200 BILLION.
THIS PIECE OF LEGISLATION PUTS
THAT MONEY AT RISK.
DONALD TRUMP RUNS FOR PRESIDENT
MAY GIVEN VLADIMIR PUTIN A
CHANCE TO GET THOSE SANCTIONS
LIFTED.
INVESTIGATORS LIKELY INTERESTED
WHETHER PUTIN, A KGB
RECRUITER, --
>> IT WOULD CAUSE AN
EMBARRASSMENT OR THREATEN.
IT IS WHAT YOU USE TO HANG OVER
SOMEBODY'S HEAD AS A MEAN TO
CONTROL.
>> A DEPUTY OF ASSISTANT OF
STATE FOCUSED ON INTERNATIONAL
ORGANIZED CRIMES IN THE 1990s.
>> IT IS ALMOST, ALWAYS OR TWO
KINDS OF THINGS, IT IS EITHER
FINANCIAL COMPROMISE, YOU TAKEN
A PAYMENT FROM SOMEONE YOU DO
NOT REPORT OR YOU HAVE DONE
SEXUALLY THAT YOU CAN'T HAVE IT
DISCLOSE.
THE RUSSIANS LOOK FOR A CORRUPT
BUSINESSMAN AND A TARGET
COUNTRY.
THEY SEEK COMPROMISE THAT
CORRUPT BUSINESS PERSON.
AND INJECT THAT CORRUPT BUSINESS
PERSON LIKE A VIRUS INTO THE
POLITICAL BUSINESS STRUCTURE OF
A COUNTRY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WHETHER DONALD TRUMP HAD BEEN
COMPROMISED BY RUSSIAN
INTELLIGENCE IS A CORE MYSTERY
OF THE MUELLER INVESTIGATION.
THE PRESIDENT HAS REPEATEDLY
DENIED HE HAS BUSINESS TIES TO
RUSSIA.
BUT FINANCIAL TRANSACTIONS IN
THE MID 2000S AND COMMENTS BY
HIS OWN FAMILY SUGGESTS OTHER
WISE.
>> STARTING AROUND 2006, THE
TRUMP AND THE TRUMP ORGANIZATION
GOING ON SHOPPING SPREES AND
SPENDING A LOT OF CASH AND A
NUMBER OF ACQUISITION INCLUDING
MAJOR GOLF COURSE IN SCOTLAND.
THERE IS A QUESTION AROUND WHERE
DID THEY GET THE MONEY TO DO
THIS.
IN 2008, DONALD TRUMP JR. STATED
THAT RUSSIA WAS AN IMPORTANT
FINANCIAL PARTNER.
>> DONALD TRUMP JR. SAYS IN THE
2008 CONFERENCE QUOTE, "RUSSIANS
MAKE UP A PRETTY
DISPROPORTIONATE CROSS-SECTION
OF A LOT OF OUR ASSETS."
WE SEE A LOT OF MONEY POURING IN
FROM RUSSIA.
>> ERIC TRUMP TOLD JAMES DODSON
THE SAME THING.
>> ERIC TRUMP SUGGESTED TO A
WELL REGARDED CALL THAT THOSE
FUNDING CAME FROM RUSSIA.
>> ERIC TRUMP TOLD THE NEW YORK
POST THAT HE WAS MISQUOTED,
STATING THE ALLEGATIONS WAS
QUOTE, "COMPLETE GARBAGE."
DONALD TRUMP HAD BEEN TO RUSSIA
MORE THAN ONCE.
HE FIRST WENT TO 1987 WHEN IT IS
STILL THE SOVIET UNION, HE
RETURNED IN 1996.
HIS CONNECTION WITH RUSSIA GREW
DEEPLY WHEN A RUSSIAN OLIGARCH
HELPED HIM STAGE THE PAGEANT IN
RUSSIA.
>> WE MET AGUILAR IN MOSCOW AND
HE CAME UP TO US AND RECEIVED A
WARM WELCOME.
>> ROB GOLD STONE IS A PUBLICIST
WHO WORKS FOR AGUILAR.
>> MR. TRUMP SAYS HE BELIEVES
THAT THE RUSSIANS HAD A STRONG
LEADER IN PRESIDENT PUTIN UNLIKE
AMERICA WHOSE LEADER WAS WEAK.
>> DONALD TRUMP EXPRESSED HOPE
ON TWITTER THAT HE AND PUTIN
WOULD BECOME BEST FRIENDS.
IN NOVEMBER OF 2013, SOON AFTER
THE PAGEANT ENDED, DONALD TRUMP
ANNOUNCED HIS DREAMS OF BUILDING
A TOWER IN MOSCOW BEARING HIS
NAME.
HE ENTRUSTED THE DEAL TO HIS
RIGHT HAND MAN AND PERSONAL
FIXER, MICHAEL COHEN.
>> AT SOME POINT IN 2015, THE
TRUMP ORGANIZATION BEGAN TO TRY
TO TAKE ACTION AROUND BUILDING A
MAJOR SKYSCRAPER IN MOSCOW.
MICHAEL COHEN WAS A KEY FORCE IN
PLANNING THAT THOUGHT IN THE
PRESIDENT'S EARS.
TRUMP HAD A FINANCIAL INTEREST
IN TRYING TO GET SOMETHING DONE
IN RUSSIA AT THE VERY MOMENT
WHEN TRUMP HIMSELF WAS A
CANDIDATE FOR THE MOST POWERFUL
OFFICE IN THE WORLD.
>> BUT EVEN AS CANDIDATE TRUMP
DENIED BUSINESS TIES TO RUSSIA,
CONFIDENTIAL REPORTS CLAIMING
OTHERWISE SURFACED IN
WASHINGTON, D.C.
>> WHAT'S KNOWN AS THE STEELE
DOSSIER IS NAMED FOR THE BRITISH
INTELLIGENCE TO COMPILE ITS
CONTENT.
>> THE STEELE DOSSIER IS
COLLECTION OF TIPS COMPILED BY
BRITISH AGENTS WHO WAS HIRED BY
REPUBLICAN CAMPAIGNS AND BY
HILLARY CLINTON CAMPAIGN TO FIND
OUT WHAT'S GOING ON WITH DONALD
TRUMP RUSSIA.
>> STEEL BEGAN HIS INVESTIGATION
IN THE FALL OF 2015 AND
CONTINUED INTO 2016.
IN JUNE, STEEL'S FIRST REPORT
SUGGESTED THAT RUSSIA HAD
COMPROMISED AND THEN CANDIDATE
TRUMP INCLUDING ALLEGEDLY
COMPROMISING FINANCIAL AND
SEXUAL INFORMATION.
>> I MET WITH STEEL AND HE KNEW
MORE ABOUT RUSSIA ORGANIZE
CRIMES THAN I DID.
I KNEW A LOT BUT HE KNEW MORE.
THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT HAD A
RELATIONSHIP WITH DONALD TRUMP
OF ONGOING CONTACTS BETWEEN
DONALD TRUMP AND THOSE CLOSE IN
THE RUSSIA GOVERNMENT.
>> STEEL'S REPORT GREW MORE
ALARMING.
>> STEEL HEARING OF THE FACT
THAT RUSSIA WAS DANGLING DEALS
WITH TRUMP.
HE KNEW THE NAMES LIKE MICHAEL
COHEN AND FELIX SATER.
IT WAS TOTALLY OUTSIDE THE
EXPERIENCES OF ANYTHING THAT
ANYONE HAD EVER HEARD ABOUT A
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE.
SOME OF THE DOSSIERS HAVE BEEN
CORROBORATED BUT MUCH OF IT HAS
NOT INCLUDING ITS SEXUAL
ALLEGATIONS.
IN THE CLOSING DAYS OF 2016 AS
PRESIDENT OBAMA STRUGGLED TO
RESPOND TO A PRESIDENT ASSAULT,
THE STEELE DOSSIER WAS LARGELY
UNKNOWN TO THE PUBLIC.
BY THE TIME IT WAS PUBLIC TO
BUZZ FEED IN 2016, DONALD TRUMP
HAD ALREADY WON THE ELECTION.
>> I AM VERY CONCERNED.
>> I AM CONCERNED THAT DONALD
TRUMP IS BEHAVING LIKE SOMEONE
WHO MAY HAVE BEEN COMPROMISED OR
BLACKMAILED BY RUSSIA.
THAT'S SOMETHING WE NEED TO GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF.
WE NEED TO GE
TO THE BOTTOM OF
COMING UP.
>> WE HAVE THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES LITERALLY
DEFENDING THE PRESIDENT OF
RUSSIA.
I switched to
Liberty Mutual
because they let me
customize my insurance,
and as a fitness junkie,
I customize everything.
Like my bike and my calves.
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance
so you only pay for
what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>>> I THINK I GET ALONG VERY
WELL WITH VLADIMIR PUTIN.
I THINK I GET ALONG WELL WITH
HIM.
WHILE THE MUELLER INVESTIGATION
NEARS THE TWO-YEAR MARK AND NO
INFORMATION ABOUT ITS FINDINGS
ARE AVAILABLE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND HIS WHITE
HOUSE REPEATEDLY STATED THERE
WAS NO COLLUSION BETWEEN HIS
PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN AND
RUSSIA.
>> THERE WAS NO COLLUSION.
>> NO COLLUSION.
>> EVIDENCE OF CONTACT BETWEEN
RUSSIA AND HIS FAMILY AND
ASSOCIATES AND DONALD TRUMP
HIMSELF.
ONE EVENT STANDS ABOVE THE REST
AS EVIDENT POTENTIAL COLLUSION
BETWEEN THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND
RUSSIAN OPERATES.
THE MEETING OF JUNE 9th, 2016 AT
TRUMP TOWER.
>> WHO WAS TRUMP'S CLOSEST
BUSINESS ASSOCIATES IN RUSSIA?
THE GUY HE DID MISS UNIVERSE
WITH.
SO IF YOU WANT TO GET A MESSAGE
TO THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN FROM THE
RUSSIA'S SIDE, THOSE ARE THE
PEOPLE WHO YOU GO TO.
>> ROB GOLDSTEIN, A PUBLICIST
ORCHESTRATED THE EVENT AND WOULD
NOT ATTEND THE MEETING.
THE MESSAGE TO HIS E-MAIL NO
DONALD TRUMP JR. WOULD LATER
RAISE EYE BROWS.
>> SOME OFFICIALS DOCUMENTS AND
INFORMATION THAT'LL IN CRIMINATE
HILLARY.
>> DON JR. WOULD LATER IGNITE A
FIRE STORM OF CONTROVERSY.
>> HE SAYS I LOVE IT.
IT BECOMES PART OF THE EVIDENCE
RECORD THAT KNEW AND TRYING TO
GET DIRT WITH HILLARY CLINTON IN
KAHOOT WITH RUSSIAN NATIONALS.
>> WHEN YOU TELL SOMEONE WE HAVE
DIRT ON HILLARY AND YOU ARE
TESTING THE WATERS TO SEE WHAT
THE RESPONSE IS AND ONCE YOU GET
A YES, A POSITIVE RESPONSE TO
THAT.
YOU HAVE HOOKED YOUR FISH.
>> JOINING DON JR. AT THE
MEETING, DONALD TRUMP'S
SON-IN-LAW, JARED KUSHNER AND
CAMPAIGN CHAIRMAN PAUL MANAFORT,
THE POWERFUL POLITICAL
CONSULTANT WITH TIES TO RUSSIA.
IT  INCLUDES NATHIALI BUTINA.
>> THE QUESTION HAD ALWAYS BEEN
DID CANDIDATE TRUMP KNEW ABOUT
THE MEETING FROM HAPPENING?
>> IF TRUMP KNEW AND DID IN THE
STOP IT FROM HAPPENING, THAT IN
ITSELF IS A CRIME EVEN IF HE DID
NOT ASK OR DIRECT IT.
>> IF DONALD TRUMP JR. AND JARED
KUSHNER TOOK THIS MEETING
INNOCENTLY AND IGNORANTLY IS
POSSIBLE.
MR. MANAFORT WOULD KNOW.
ALTHOUGH THE MEETING REPORTEDLY
DIDN'T DELIVER ANY IN
CRIMINATING INFORMATION, IT DID
CAUSE PROBLEMS FOR DON JR. WHEN
CONTACTED BY THE NEW YORK TIMES,
RELEASED A SHORT STATEMENT THAT
THE MEETING WAS PRIMARILY ABOUT
RUSSIAN ADOPTION.
WHEN THE "TIMES" FOLLOWED UP, HE
CHANGED HIS EXPLANATION.
>> DONALD TRUMP RELEASING
E-MAILS THAT CONFIRMED HE MET
LAST YEAR WITH SOMEONE DESCRIBED
AS A RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT
ATTORNEY.
IT WAS LATER REPORTED THAT THE
PRESIDENT DICTATED JOHN JR.'S
ORIGINAL STATEMENT ABOUT
ADOPTION.
>> DON JR. PUTS THE LIE OUT, HE
KNEW HE WAS GOING TO A MEETING
TO GET DIRT FROM HILLARY CLINTON
FROM A RUSSIAN NATIONAL WHICH I
CAN'T SAY OFTEN ENOUGH BECAUSE
THAT'S JUST DAMMING.
>> HAD THEY JUST EXPLAIN
EVERYTHING?
HAD THOSE E-MAILS BEEN RELEASED
BY DON JR. FROM THE BEGINNING?
>> THERE IS NO THERE THERE.
IT IS BECAUSE THEY LIED THAT
MAKES IT LOOKED MORE SIGNIFICANT
THAN IT IS.
>> AS THE CAMPAIGN CONTINUES SO
DID CONTACTS BETWEEN TRUMP
ASSOCIATES AND RUSSIAN
INDIVIDUALS.
AFTER WINNING THE ELECTION, THE
PRESIDENT-ELECT TRUMP PRORUSSIA
STATEMENTS RAISED CONCERNS.
>> IF PUTIN LIKES DONALD TRUMP,
GUESS WHAT, FOLKS, THAT'S CALLED
AN ASSET, NOT A LIABILITY.
IN 2018, WHEN PRESIDENT TRUMP
CRITICIZED AMERICAN ALLIES IN
THE EUROPEAN UNION AND BARBED
THE U.S.'S ROLE IN NATO.
>> WE ARE GOING TO HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING BECAUSE WE ARE NOT
GOING TO PUT UP WITH IT.
>> HIS WORDS SENT SHOCK WAVES
AROUND THE WORLD BECAUSE A WEEK
IN NATO WHICH WAS CREATED TO
PROTECT AGAINST RUSSIAN
AGGRESSION COULD STRENGTHEN
PUTIN'S INFLUENCE.
THE UNUSUAL RELATIONSHIP
CONTINUED TO EVALUATE AND IN
JULY 2018, DURING THE HELSINKI
MEETING, THE PRESIDENT WAS PUT
IN THE SPOT IN THE ENTIRE WORLD.
>> EVERY U.S. INTELLIGENCE
COMPUTED THAT RUSSIA DID
INTERFERED.
MY FIRST QUESTION TO YOU, SIR,
WHO DO YOU BELIEVE?
>> PEOPLE CAME TO ME AND THEY
SAID THEY THINK IT IS RUSSIA.
I HAVE PRESIDENT PUTIN, HE JUST
SAID IT IS NOT RUSSIA.
I WILL SAY THIS, I DON'T SEE ANY
REASON WHY IT WOULD BE.
>> WE HAVE THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES LITERALLY
DEFENDING THE PRESIDENT OF
RUSSIA.
TELLING THE WORLD THAT HIS OWN
INTELLIGENCE APPARATUS IS NOT
RIGHT.
THAT'S ASTOUNDING.
>> DESPITE STATING THAT HE
MISSPOKE THE NEXT DAY.
>> I SAID THE WORD "WOULD,"
INSTEAD OF "WOULDN' T."
PEOPLE ARE SPEAKING OUT IN WAYS
I HAVE NOT HEARD BEFORE, NOT
ONLY AMERICAN DIPLOMATS BUT
FOREIGN DIPLOMATS WHO WERE
SAYING WE CAN'T RELY ON THE
PRESIDENT.
>> TO ME THAT'S SOMETHING HE
WOULD HAVE TO LOOK INTO.
THE PRESIDENT HAD GONE TO GREAT
LENGTHS TO CONCEAL THE DETAILS
OF THE PRIVATE HELSINKI MEETING
AS HE HAS FOR EACH OF THE FOUR
PRIVATE MEETINGS HE HAD WITH
VLADIMIR PUTIN, LEADING MANY TO
ASK, IS THIS A BROMANCE OR
SOMETHING ELSE?
>> I DON'T LIKE THE TERM
BROMANCE BECAUSE THAT IMPLIES
THERE IS A MUTUAL RELATIONSHIP.
>> I THINK DONALD TRUMP IS
HANDLING A SPY AND TO SIT WITH
AN EX KGB WHO'S THE LEADER OF
THE GREATEST MAFIA IN THE WORLD,
YOU ARE GOING TO GET HANDLED AND
NOT JUST HANDLED, HE'S GOING TO
MANIPULATE YOU AND YOU WOULD
THINK IT IS A BROMANCE, HE WILL
THINK THAT HE'S NOW IN CONTROL
OF THE UNITED STATES.
>> COMING UP.
>> MR. STONE TOLD MR. TRUMP THAT
HE JUST GOTTEN OFF THE PHONE
WITH JULIAN ASSANGE.
>> WE JUST DON'T KNOW AND IF HE
KNEW IT FOR CERTAIN, HOW HE KNEW
IT FOR CERTAIN.
...we're open
just pass the ball!
No, I can't believe how easy it
was to save hundreds of dollars
on my car
insurance with GEICO.
Yea.
[QUARTET SINGING]
Shoot the J! Shoot, shoot,
shoot the jaaaaaay...
Believe it! GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
or more on car insurance.
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it from
your allergy pills?
Flonase Sensimist relieves
all your worst symptoms,
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
And all from a gentle mist
you can barely feel.
Flonase Sensimist.
DEALDASH.COM, THE FAIR AND
HONEST BIDDING SITE. AN IPAD WAS
SOLD FOR LESS THAN $24; A
PLAYSTATION FOR LESS THAN $16;
AND A 4K TELEVISION FOR LESS
THAN $2. GO TO DEALDASH.COM
RIGHT NOW AND SEE HOW MUCH YOU
CAN SAVE. REMEMBER, SHIPPING IS
ALWAWA
Termites,
feasting on homes 24/7.
We're on the move.
Roger.
Hey Rick, all good?
Oh yeah, we're good.
We're good.
Termites never stop trying to
get in,
we never stop working to keep
them out.
Terminix.
Defenders of Home.
>>> I AM RICHARD LUI, 157 PEOPLE
ARE DEAD AFTER THE ETHIOPIAN
AIRLINES TOOK OFF.
SAFETY EXPERTS ARE TRAVELING TO
THE COUNTRY TO HELP IN THE
INVESTIGATION.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WILL DELIVER HIS
PRESIDENT ADDRESS ON MONDAY
ASKING FOR $8.5 BILLION TO BUILD
HIS WALL.
NOW BACK TO "RUSSIA, IF YOU ARE
LISTENING."
>> A NUMBER OF PEOPLE AROUND
THIS CAMPAIGN WITH TIES FROM
RUSSIA.
PEOPLE DO NOT SEEM TO BE LYING
ABOUT SPAIN OR NETHERLANDS OR
ITALY OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
IT IS RUSSIA.
>> SINCE THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION BEGAN, HIS OFFICE
OBTAINED CONVICTIONS OF FIVE
ASSOCIATES OF DONALD TRUMP.
THE CHARGES HAVE RANGED FROM
LYING TO THE FBI TO TAX
EVASIONS.
THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S FILINGS
HAVE MADE IT CLEAR THAT ALL FIVE
HAD SUSPICIOUS CONTACTS WITH
RUSSIA DURING THE CAMPAIGN.
>> THERE IS A LOT OF EFFORTS BY
THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT TO TAMPER
IN THE INTERFERENCE.
>> A SIXTH INDICTMENT CAME IN
JANUARY 2019 AGAINST ROGER STONE
FOR MAKING FALSE STATEMENTS TO
CONGRESS AND OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE AND WITNESS TAMPERING.
STONE PLEADED NOT GUILTY.
>> THERE IS NO CIRCUMSTANCE
WHATSOEVER UNDER WHICH I BARE
FAULT WITNESS.
>> ROGER STONE IS WILLING TO
COLOR OUTSIDE THE LINES IN A WAY
THAT OTHER STRATEGISTS OR OTHER
POLITICAL OPERATIVES MAY BE
UNWILLING TO DO.
>> STONE WAS NOT A MEMBER OF THE
TRUMP CAMPAIGN STAFF, HE SERVED
AS AN UNOFFICIAL ADVISER.
HE CAME TO MUELLER AFTER
BRAGGING IN 2016 THAT HE WAS
COMMUNICATING DIRECTLY WITH
WIKILEAKS FOUNDER, JULIAN
ASSANGE.
ASSANGE BECAME A FACTOR OF JUNE
2016 WHEN HE MADE AN
ANNOUNCEMENT ON BRITISH
TELEVISION.
>> WE HAVE E-MAILS ABOUT HILLARY
CLINTON.
ACCORDING TO FORMER TRUMP'S
LAWYER, MICHAEL COHEN, BEFORE
WIKILEAKS RELEASED ANY OF THOSE
E-MAILS, ROGER STONE CALLED
DONALD TRUMP.
MR. STONE TOLD MR. TRUMP, HE
GOTTEN OFF THE PHONE WITH MR.
JULIAN ASSANGE.
MR. ASSANGE TOLD MR. STONE THAT
IN A COUPLE OF DAYS, THERE WILL
BE A MASSIVE DUMP OF E-MAILS
THAT WOULD DAMAGE HILLARY
CLINTON'S CAMPAIGN.
>> THAT'S ROGER TRYING TO BE
REMAINING RELEVANT TO TRUMP.
>> SOON AFTER THAT ALLEGED PHONE
CALL, WIKILEAKS BEGAN ITS FIRST
DUMP OF HACK MATERIAL.
>> THIS WEEKEND, WIKILEAKS
RELEASED NEARLY 20,000 E-MAILS
SENT AND RECEIVED BY MEMBERS OF
DEMOCRATIC NATIONAL COMMITTEE.
CAMERAS CAPTURED STONE ON AUGUST
8th, TELLING AN AUDIENCE IN
SOUTHERN FLORIDA ABOUT HIS
CONNECTION WITH ASSANGE.
>> I HAVE COMMUNICATED WITH
ASSANGE.
ON OCTOBER 7th, THE DAY OF THE
INFAMOUS "ACCESS HOLLYWOOD"
TAPE.
>> A MASSIVE DOCUMENT DUMP FROM
WIKILEAKS OF WHAT APPEARS TO BE
HACKED E-MAILS FROM CLINTON'S
CAMPAIGN, JOHN PODESTA'S G-MAIL
ACCOUNT.
>> ACCORDING TO HIS INDICTMENT,
HE RECEIVED A MESSAGE FROM THE
CAMPAIGN OFFICIAL SAYING
WELL-DONE.
>> SINCE 2016, ROGER STONE
DENIED SPEAKING DIRECTLY WITH
JULIAN ASSANGE.
>> THERE IS NO SUGGESTION OR ANY
COURT DOCUMENTS THAT ROGER STONE
WAS DIRECTLY IN TOUCH WITH
ASSANGE.
>> STONE MAY HAVE HAD DIRECT
DEALINGS WITH JULIAN ASSANGE.
THAT'S NOT MUTUALLY EXCLUSIVE.
THE CENTRAL QUESTION WHETHER THE
RUSSIANS CONSPIRE WITH TRUMP OR
WITH HIS CAMPAIGN OR OFFICIALS
ON THAT CAMPAIGN INTERFERE IN
OUR ELECTION.
>> STONE HAS JOINED THE GROWING
LIST OF TRUMP'S ASSOCIATES.
GEORGE PAPADOPOULOS, A FOREIGN
POLICY OF THE CAMPAIGN CONVICTED
O F LYING TO THE FBI.
HE MET WITH RUSSIAN INTELLIGENCE
OFFICERS WHO TOLD HIM THE
RUSSIANS HAD HILLARY CLINTON'S
MISSING E-MAILS.
>> WE DON'T KNOW WHO IN THE
TRUMP CAMPAIGN HE INFORMED, HE
CLAIMED HE DID NOT REMEMBER WHO
HE SHARED WITH.
HE ONCE TOLD ME ROBERT MUELLER
KNOWS.
>> THE CLUES CAME OUT IN A
RECENT FILINGS BY PAUL
MANAFORT'S ATTORNEY.
>> MANAFORT SHARED POLLING DATA
THROUGH KILIMNIK WHO HAS WORKED
FOR RUSSIAN INTELLIGENCE AND
THEY PASSED THAT POLLING DATA
OFF DURING THE CAMPAIGN.
>> THIS IS THE BEST EXAMPLE THAT
WE HAVE SEEN, WHY WOULD A RUSSIA
NEED INTERNAL POLLING DATA IF
NOT TO HELP TO MANIPULATE THE
ELECTION.
OTHER PEOPLE SAY IT COULD BE
NOTHING.
>> THE LARGER QUESTION MAY BE
HOW SO MANY PEOPLE IN ONE
CAMPAIGN ENDED UP COMMUNICATING
WITH RUSSIA.
>> AGAIN AND AGAIN AND AGAIN AT
WHAT HAPPENS IN THIS PARTICULAR
INVESTIGATION ARE TIES TO
RUSSIA.
IS THAT AN ACCIDENT?
I DON'T THINK SO.
>> COMING UP, THE PRESIDENT
FIGHTS ROBERT MUELLER AT EVERY
TURN.
Last years' ad campaign
was a success for
ChoiceHotels.com
Badda Book. Badda Boom.
This year, we're taking it
up a notch.
So in this commercial we see
two travelers
at a Comfort INN with a glow
around them,
so people watching will be like,
"wow, maybe I'll glow
too if I book direct
at ChoiceHotels.com".
Who glows?
Just say, Badda Book.
Badda Boom.
Nobody glows.
He gets it.
Always the lowest price,
guaranteed.
Book now at ChoiceHotels.com
No more excuses
with Cologuard.
We all make excuses for the
things we don't want to do.
But when it comes to
colon cancer screening...
I'm not doin' that.
I eat plenty of kale.
Ahem, as I was saying...
...with Cologuard,
you don't need an excuse...
All that prep?
No thanks.
That drink tastes horrible!
But...there's no
prep with Cologuard...
I can't take the
time off work.
Who has two days?
And I feel fine -
no symptoms!
Everybody, listen!
All you need is a
trip to the bathroom.
If you're 50 or older
and at average risk,
Cologuard is the
noninvasive option
that finds 92%
of colon cancers.
You just get the
kit in the mail,
go to the bathroom,
collect your sample,
then ship it to the lab!
This is your year!
Own it!
Cologuard is not right
for everyone.
It is not for high
risk individuals,
including those with a
history of colon cancer
or precancer, IBD, certain
hereditary cancer syndromes,
or a family history
of colon cancer.
Ask your doctor if Cologuard
is right for you.
Covered by Medicare and
most major insurers.
>>> FAKE NEWS OF THE RUSSIAN
WITCH HUNT.
>> SINCE TAKING OFF IN 2017,
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS PUBLICLY
ATTACKED THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION, LED BY SPECIAL
COUNSEL ROBERT MUELLER MORE THAN
A THOUSAND TIMES.
>>> THE PRESIDENT IS TAKING ALL
KINDS OF STEPS TO UNDERMINE THE
FBI AND LAW ENFORCEMENT.
>> HE DISPARAGES FACT FINDINGS
AND DISPARAGES ANYONE WHO SAYS
ANYTHING HE DOES NOT LIKE.
HE CALLS THEM LIARS.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING IS A
DISGRACE AND AT SOME POINT I
WANT TO STAY OUT BUT AT SOME
POINT IF IT DOES NOT STRAIGHTEN
OUT PROPERLY, I WANT THEM TO DO
THEIR JOB, I WILL GET INVOLVED
AND I WILL GET IN THERE IF I
HAVE TO.
>> HE ARGUED THAT THE FBI IS
LOOKING AT HIM WHEN THEY SHOULD
BE LOOKING AT HILLARY CLINTON
AND HE CAN WHIP UP HIS
SUPPORTERS AT HIS RALLY WHEN HE
TALKS ABOUT THE INVESTIGATION
AND PAINTS HIMSELF AS SOMEONE
BEING VICTIMIZED BY THIS.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP'S ARGUMENT IS
THAT MUELLER AND HIS TEAM ARE
OUT TO GET HIM FOR PURELY
POLITICAL REASONS.
>> I CALL HIM THE ANGRY
DEMOCRAT.
IT IS AN UNFAIR THING FOR THIS
COUNTRY.
>> HE BEGAN RIGHT AT THE
BEGINNING ATTACKING
INVESTIGATIONS ON THE GROUND
THAT MUELLER SURROUNDED HIMSELF
WITH DEMOCRATS AND WITHOUT
KNOWING THE FACT THAT THERE WERE
REPUBLICANS.
ROBERT MUELLER IS A REGISTERED
REPUBLICAN.
>> ROBERT MUELLER REMAINED TIGHT
LIFT.
>> WORKING FOR MUELLER, SOMEONE
WHO DO NOT TOLERATE AND WOULD
NEVER AUTHORIZE ANY TYPE OF LEAK
TO THE MEDIA.
HE HAD SUCH A REPUTATION IN THAT
REGARD.
>> IT IS NOT ONLY LAW
ENFORCEMENT TARGETED IN TRUMP'S
ATTACKS.
THE PRESIDENT TRUMP TRIED TO
DISCREDIT WITNESSES, EVEN THOSE
IN HIS INNER CIRCLE INCLUDING
MICHAEL COHEN.
>> HE TRIES TO INTIMIDATE, HE
CALLS MICHAEL COHEN A RAT AND A
SNITCH.
WHO TALKS LIKE THAT?
>> AT FIRST WHEN THE FBI
SEARCHED MICHAEL COHEN'S HOME,
HOTEL AND OFFICE IN APRIL OF
2018, THE PRESIDENT DEFENDED
COHEN.
>> I JUST HEARD THAT THEY BROKE
INTO THE OFFICE OF MICHAEL
COHEN'S, ONE OF MY PERSONAL
ATTORNEYS, GOOD MAN.
IT IS A DISGRACEFUL SITUATION
AND IT IS A TOTAL WITCH HUNT.
I HAVE BEEN SAYING IT FOR A LONG
TIME.
AUGUST 21st, 2018, A
CONSEQUENTIAL DATE FOR THE
PRESIDENT WITHIN HOURS FOR PAUL
MANAFORT'S CONVICTION IN FEDERAL
COURT.
COHEN PLEADED GUILTY IN
CONNECTION WITH HUSH MONEY
PAYMENT MADE DURING THE CAMPAIGN
TO TWO WOMEN WHO CLAIMED AFFAIRS
WITH DONALD TRUMP.
PRESIDENT TRUMP DENIED HE HAD AN
AFFAIR WITH STORMY DANIELS AND
WHEN IT CAME TO THE ALLEGED
AFFAIR WITH PLAYBOY MODEL KAREN
McDOUGAL, THE WHITE HOUSE CALLED
IT WHITE HOUSE CALLED IT FAKE
NEWS.
IN LATE NOVEMBER ANOTHER TOUGH
DAY FOR THE PRESIDENT.
MICHAEL COHEN AGREED TO
COOPERATE WITH THE RUSSIA PROBE.
DRAWING THE PRESIDENT'S IRE.
>> HE'S A WEAK PERSON.
WHAT HE IS TRYING TO DO IS GET A
REDUCED SENTENCE.
HE'S LYING.
>> ONE OF THE PRESIDENT'S
PATTERN HAS BEEN CRITICIZE
PEOPLE WHO HAVE BEEN COOPERATING
WITH MUELLER OR TESTIFYING
CALLING THM LIARS AND WEAK.
SAYING THEY WANT TO CUT DEALS
JUST TO SAVE THEIR OWN SKIN.
AND YOU HAVE THE SELF-INFLICTED
WOUNDS THE FBI BROUGHT UPON
ITSELF.
>> GRILLING ROSENSTEIN OVER TEXT
MESSAGES.
>> ONE OF THE OFFICIALS WAS
PETER STRZOK.
HE LED THE INVESTIGATION TO 2016
INTO HILLARY CLINTONS MISSING
E-MAILS BEFORE BEING ASSIGNED TO
THE RUSSIA PROBE ALONG WITH LISA
PAGE THE FOLLOWS YEAR.
>> THEY WERE TEXTING ONE
ANOTHER.
MANY TIMES A DAY ON FBI DEVICES.
SOME TEXTS WERE CRITICAL OF
DONALD TRUMP AND ERUPTED INTO A
SCANDAL.
>> WE HAVE THEIR TEXT MESSAGES.
WHAT THEY SAID WAS SHOCKING.
WHEN YOU THOUGHT ABOUT BIAS.
>> THIS WAS CATNIP FOR TRUMP.
PARTISAN DEMOCRATS ATTACKING ME.
I TOLD YOU THIS WAS A WITCH
HUNT.
>> THE MEDIA IS ALSO A FREQUENT
TARGET OF PRESIDENT TRUMP
ATTACKS.
>> THEY ARE THE FAKE DISGUSTING
NEWS.
>> IT'S RIGHT OUT OF PUTIN'S
PLAY BOOK HOW HE HANDLES THE
MEDIA.
TRYING TO MAKE IT AWE'RE
EVERYTHING THEY PRINT IS FAKE
AND NOT THE REAL NEWS.
>> MOST HARD CORE TRUMP
SUPPORTERS ACCEPTED HIS FRAME
THAT EVERYTHING OF WHAT THE
RUSSIA INFORMATION IS FAKE AND
TUNE IT OUT.
>>> COMING UP.
WHATEVER IS IN THE MUELLER
REPORT, THERE ARE STILL OTHER
LEGAL CHALLENGES THAT THE
PRESIDENT FACES.
>> THAT WOULD SEND CHILLS DOWN
MY SPINE.
Look LiMu. A civilian
buying a new car.
Let's go.
LiMu's right.
Liberty Mutual can
save you money
by customizing your
car insurance,
so you only pay for
what you need.
Oh... yeah, I've been a
customer for years.
Huh...
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
Guys do whatever it takes to
deal with shave irritation.
So, we re-imagined the razor
with the new Gillette SkinGuard.
It has a unique guard
between the blades.
That's designed to reduce
irritation during the shave.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
Gillette.
With tough food, your dentures
may slip and fall.
Fixodent Ultra-Max Hold
gives you the strongest hold
ever
to lock your dentures.
So now you can eat tough food
without worry.
Fixodent and forget it.
Stop fearing your alarm clock...
With ZzzQuil PURE Zzzs.
A drug-free blend of botanicals
with melatonin
that supports your natural sleep
cycle
so you can seize the morning.
ZzzQuil PURE Zzzs.
>>> IT'S BEEN ONE OF THE MOST
ANALYZED, SCRUTINIZED, AND
CRITICIZED INVESTIGATIONS IN
MODERN POLITICAL HISTORY.
>> WASHINGTON IS NOW IN EAGER
ANTICIPATION MODE FOR THE
COMPLETION OF THE MUELLER
REPORT.
>> IT'S EXPECTED THAT THE REPORT
WILL SOON BE IN THE HANDS OF
ATTORNEY GENERAL WILLIAM BAR.
ANY POTENTIAL HISTORY ALTERING
CONTENTS ARE A MYSTERY.
SO WHEN THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
GETS IT, THEN WHAT?
>> HE'S GOING TO REVIEW IT AND
MAKE SURE THAT THERE'S NOT
SENSITIVE INFORMATION GRAND JURY
MATERIAL.
SOURCES AND METHODS THAT ARE
CLASSIFIED.
THERE MAYBE A PLAUSIBLE CLAIM OF
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE.
WITH RESPECT TO THE MATERIAL.
>> SOMETIMES CRIMINAL
INVESTIGATIONS CAN HURT THE
PRIVACY AND TRUST OF INDIVIDUALS
AND THE EXAMPLE WE WERE DEALING
WITH IN REALTIME IN 1999 WAS THE
LIEU INSKI ALLEGATION DUMPED ON
CONGRESS.
FOR THAT REASON WE GAVE THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL DISCRETION OVER
WHAT TO GIVE TO CONGRESS.
>> THE REGULATIONS DON'T MAKE
CLEAR EXACTLY HOW THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL IF AT ALL WILL SUMMARIZE
THE MUELLER REPORT.
HE COULD HAVE A NEWS CONFERENCE
AND TALK ABOUT IT.
WRITE HIS OWN REPORT.
>> WE HAVE TO SEE WAS THERE
ENOUGH EVIDENCE TO CONVICT?
OR WASN'T THERE.
YOU CAN'T SAY THERE WASN'T
ENOUGH EVIDENCE.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO FLY.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO THINK BAR IS
GOING TO ACT IN THE PUBLIC
ENTLES AND RELEASE AS MUCH AS
CONGRESS NEEDS TO MAKE THE
DECISION THAT WILL HAVE BEFORE
IT.
>> EVEN IF THE ENTIRE REPORT IS
RELEASED TO THE PUBLIC UNED ITD,
THE CONTENT MAY NOT REVEAL ALL
THAT MUCH.
IT'S GOING TO BE VERY SPARE.
IF MUELLER STICKS TO THE RULES
AND IF THERE'S ONE THING MUELLER
TENDS TO DO IT'S STICK TO THE
RULES.
>> REGULATIONS SAY THAT'S
SUMMARY SHOULD BE VERY BRIEF.
IF HE STICKS TO THE LETTER OF
THE REGULAR.
THERE WILL BE UNHAPPY PEOPLE.
>> ONE POSSIBLE REASON IS ROBERT
MUELLER COULD BE GIVE B A ROAD
MAP TO FUTURE INVESTIGATIONS.
THAT DON'T HAVE THE LIMITED
SCOPE HE'S BEEN WORKING UNDER
AND HANDING THEM DOCUMENTED
EVIDENCE OF POSSIBLE CRIMINAL
BEHAVIOR.
>> THE STATES THE LOCAL DISTRICT
ATTORNEY, CONGRESS, AND U.S.
ATTORNEYS OFFICES ALL MAYBE
PICKING UP ON DIFFERENT
INVESTIGATIVE LEADS.
>> THE HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE
CHAIRMAN NADLER SENT LETTERS TO
81 INDIVIDUALS EXPANDING THAT ON
THE INVESTIGATION AND LOOKING TO
THESE THINGS SUCH AS DONALD
TRUMP OTHERS BUSINESS DEALINGS.
>> THEY ARE INTERESTED IN
WHETHER HE HAS FINANCIAL
CONSIDERATIONS WEIGHING ON HIM
FROM FOREIGN GOVERNMENT.
INFLUENCING HIS BEHAVIOR.
THEY'RE NOT CONFINING THEMSELVES
TO THE 2016 ELECTION ANYMORE.
>> IT MAKES IT MUCH MORE
DIFFICULT TO SHUT IT DOWN.
PARTICULARLY IN THE SOUTHERN
DISTRICT OF NEW YORK.
>> WHEN WE TALK ABOUT THE
SOUTHERN DISTRICT OF NEW YORK,
THEY HAVE STILL LOOKING.
AT INFORMATION REGARDING THE
TRUMP ORGANIZATION, THE TRUMP
CHARITY AND THE REVOCABLE TRUST
AND OTHER MATTERS.
THAT WOULD SEND CHILLS DOWN MY
SPINE.
>> ANOTHER AVENUE OF INTEREST.
DOES THE PRESIDENT'S
RECOLLECTION OF EVENTS ALIGN
WITH OTHER WITNESS ACCOUNTS.
>> TRURP DIDN'T WANT TO GIVE AN
INTERVIEW TO ROBERT MUELLER AND
HE DIDN'T.
HE DID GIVE WRITTEN ANSWERS.
AND IT'S CURIOUS WHY ROBERT
MUELLER WOULD ACCEPT THAT.
AND ONE REASON WOULD BE HE CAN
PIN TRUMP DOWN TO HIS STORY.
IF THEN ROBERT MUELLER COULD
DISPROVE WITH EVIDENCE AND HAVE
DONALD TRUMP ON PERJURY.
>> WHOEVER AND WHATEVER COMING
OUT OT REPORT.
EXPECT A WHITE HOUSE REBUTLE.
>> THEY PREPARED A COUNTER
REPORT.
WHAT THEY MEAN IS ALL THE WAYS
IN WHICH THEY CAN ATTACK THE
INVESTIGATION.
THE TEXT BETWEEN THE FBI AGENT
AND THE THE AGENT HE WAS HAVING
AFFAIR.
WHERE THEY SHOWED BIAS.
THEY WANT TO SUMMARIZE IT AND
ARGUE THE INVESTIGATION IS
ILLEGITIMATE.
THAT PLAYS TO THEIR BASE.
HE CREATES AN ATMOSPHERE WHERE A
THIRD OF THE COUNTRY IS NOT
GOING TO BELIEVE ANYTHING
MUELLER SAYS.
>> THE MUELLER PROBE.
ARGUABLY THE MOST SIGNIFICANT
INVESTIGATION IN THE COUNTRY
HISTORY.
INDICTED 34 INDIVIDUALS.
THERE HAVE BEEN CONVICTIONS OF
HIGH LEVEL TRUMP ASSOCIATES.
AN