INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION.
THIS WAS A MISSION THAT
COMMENCED A LITTLE MESS THAN A
WEEK AGO
IT WAS THE FIRST TIME PRIVATELY
FUNDED SPACE FLIGHTS TO CARRY
HUMANS
THIS IS A KEY MILESTONE IN HUMAN
SPACE FLIGHT IN AMERICA'S RETURN
TO THE CAPABILITY TO DO SO
BASED ON THIS, IT WOULD LIKE
LIKE SPACEX IS ON TRACK TO START
CARRYING RESTAURANTS AS SOON AS
THIS SUMMER.
>> BEEN A BUSY COUPLE OF DAYS
FOR ELON MUSK.
GETTING FINANCING FOR THE
SHANGHAI PLANT
THAT DOES IT FOR US AT SQUAWK
ALLEY.
LET'S HEAD OVER TO THE JUDGE
>>> FIVE AND COUNTING.
THAT'S THE CURRENT LOSING STREAK
FOR STOCKS
WHAT IS THE STATE OF THE MARKET?
ARE WE TRULY AT A CROSS ROADS?
IT'S 12:00 NOON.
THIS IS THE "HALFTIME REPORT ."
>> THE BIG DEBATE IS ON.
WHERE DOES IT GO NOW
ONE PERSON IS BUYING A SOCIAL
MEDIA STOCK FACING HEAD WINDS.
A DECADE AFTER THE FAMOUS CRISIS
BOTTOM, THE FORMER CEO OF BAR
CLAY, BOB DIAMOND WEIGHS IN.
ONE ANALYST CALL THAT IT'S TIME
TO CHANGE THE CHANNEL.
WHY HE'S DOWNGRADED NETFLIX.
THE HALFTIME REPORT WITH SCOTT
WAPNER STARTSNOW
>> WELCOME AND GOOD TO HAVE YOU
WITH US ON THIS FRIDAY
JOSH BROWN, STEVE WEISS, KATE
MOORE IS HERE.
COURTNEY GIBSON IS HERE AS WELL.
STOCKS SELLING OFF THE LOWS.
CONTINUING TO REACT TO THE
UNEMPLOYMENT REPORT.
ONLY 20,000 JOBS WERE ADDED IN
THE MONTH OF FEBRUARY.
BLAME THE WEATHER OR THE
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
IT'S AN UGLY NUMBER.
THE QUESTION IS IT AN ANOMALY AS
LARRY KUDLOW AND OTHERS WOULD
HAVE YOU BELIEVE
>> WE HAVE TO TAKE IT INTO
ACCOUNT.
THERE'S A NUMBER OF SECTORS
WHERE YOU'RE SEEING SLOWING JOB
GROWTH
YOU WOULD EXPECT THAT LATE IN
THE CYCLE.
SOME OF THAT WAS AFFECTED BY THE
WORKWEEKS.
THERE'S A LOT OF OTHER
UNDERLYING WAGE PRESSURE AND HOW
COMPANIES HANDLE THAT IN A YEAR
OF SLOW AND GROWTH AND MORE
UNCERTAINTY WILL BE REALLY,
REALLY CRIMINAL FOR PROFITS OVER
THE NEXT FOUR TO FIVE QUARTERS
YOU CAN BRUSH THERE ASIDE.
YOU CAN SAY LIKE TRANSPORT HAS
BEEN WEAK.
RUSSELL HAS BEEN WEEK.
WHAT DOES IT ALL MEAN TO YOU
>> I'M AGREEING WITH BOTH KUDLOW
AND YOU AND I WHEN WE HAD THE
CONVERSATION COMING ONSET.
I THINK THIS IS AN ANOMALY
I THINK THIS IS OUT THERE
BECAUSE OF WHETHER WHICH KATE
CITED AS WELL AS THE GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN
I THINK THOSE TWO FACTORS ARE
REALLY THE MAIN DRIVERS FOR A
20,000 NUMBER THAT IS SO FAR OUT
OF WHERE WE THINK THE ECONOMY IS
RIGHT NOW.
I'M ANXIOUS TO HEAR EVERYBODY
ELSE
THINKAB
I BELIEVE THIS WAS A ONE OFF AND
WE'RE TRYING TO ESTABLISH AN UP
TREND.
WE HAVE COME BACK INTO IT.
WE HAD A COUPLE OF PULL BACKS
BUT THEY NEVER BEEN MORE THAN 2
OR 3%.
I THINK THIS IS THE SAME
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN, COURT.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU
>> CONGRATS ON YOUR BABY GIRL.
NICE TO HAVE YOU BACK.
DOES IT FEEL LIKE THAT'S WHERE
WE'RE AT IN THE MARKET
>> NO.
I AGREE WITH YOU GUYS AND
KUDLOW
I'M NOT SURE IF IT'S A FLUKE
NUMBER BUT ONE DATA POINT DOES
NOT DETERMINE WHERE WE ARE
WE HAVE TO LOOK AT THIS
COLLECTIVELY
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO FOR THE
NEXT THREE MONTHS?
>> THREE MONTH AVERAGE IS GOOD
PEOPLE SAY 20, DON'T PUT TOO
MUCH STOCK IN THAT
>> ABSOLUTELY.
ARE WE AT A CROSS ROADS?
WE'RE AT ON A INTERESTING TIME
FOR SURE WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT
THE GLOBAL ECONOMY AND THE
MARKETS.
AS MUCH AS THINGS CHANGE, THEY
DO STAY THE SAME
I THINK WE WERE HAVING THE SAME
DISCUSSION WHEN I WAS HERE IN
OCTOBER.
IS THE TRADE DEAL GOING TO MAKE
A DIFFERENCE
IS FED GOING TO MAKE A
DIFFERENCE
MAYBE SO
HOWEVER, THEY ARE BEING PATIENT.
WHAT MORE CAN YOU ASK FOR IN A
MARKET THAT WANTS CERTAINTY
VERSUS UNCERTAINTY
>> TRUMP WAS LEVERING A LITTLE
WHILE AGO FOR ALABAMA.
SAYS YOU'LL SEE A BIG SPIKE WHEN
YOU GET A TRADE DEAL
THERE'S LESS OPTIMISM TODAY THAN
AT THE START OF THE WEEK ABOUT A
DW
DEAL WITH CHINA.
HOW DO YOU SEE IT?
>> I THINK COLLECTIVELY WE
THOUGHT THAT WE'RE SELLING ON
THE NEWS
THE NARRATIVE IS THERE WAS A
TRADE DEAL
>> REALLY NOT AS CLOSE
>> NOT CLOSE
>> NOW WE'RE GETTING NEGATIVITY.
I'M SURPRISED THE MARKET IS NOT
DOWN MORE.
IT IGNORED THE BJOBS NUMBER
TODAY.
>> YOU THINK IT WAS AN ANOMALY
AS WELL?
>> I DO.
I LOOK AT IT IN THE THREE-MONTH
AVERAGE.
I THINK THAT WE STILL HAVE A
LITTLE MORE PAIN IN THE MARKET
I WAS EXCHANGING E-MAILS WITH
YOUR PARTNER LAST NIGHT.
HE CALLED THE TOP ON THE TENURE
TO THE DAY AND SO THAT'S AN
IMPORTANT NUMBER BECAUSE RIGHT
NOW SITTING BELOW 2.7, WHERE ARE
YOU GOING TO PUT YOUR MONEY?
YOU'RE GOING TO PUT IT INTO
CONNECT.
I T
-- EQUITY.
WE MAY GET A POP ON CHINA BUT
WHO KNOWS IF THAT'S SUSTAINABLE.
I THINK WE SELL OFF.
WHAT HAPPENS WITH CHINA, IT
DOESN'T HAPPEN IN A DAY.
>> TRB BASKING IN THE GLOW OF
HIS STEPH CURRY RETWEET ON
TWITTER.
>> I ALMOST DIDN'T COME HERE
TODAY.
>> RIGHTFULLY SO IF YOU CHOSE
NOT TOO.
>> YOU'VE HEARD EVERYBODY.
SPIT IT OUT IN YOUR TERMS.
>> I SPOKE TO STEPH THIS
MORNING.
LOOK, IT'S THE WORST WEEK OF
2019, BUT AT ITS LOW POINT THIS
MORNING.
WE WERE OFF 3% FROM THE HIGH
SINCE MONDAY
LET'S ALL CALM DOWN.
EVERY ONE TALKS ABOUT THERE'S A
PULL BACK.
WE'RE OVER DUE FOR A PULL BACK
IT COMES AND LIKE WHAT
>> OH, MY GOODNESS
>> I BOUGHT A STOCK ON TUESDAY
AND IT'S DOWN ON THURSDAY.
>> YOU WERE IN THE RETEST CAMP
ARE YOU NO LONGER BECAUSE OF
THE --
>> MY OPINION IS WORTHLESS
ILIP-FLOPPED
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE FEBRUARY I
SAID I FEEL MORE STRONGLY.
I TRY TO PAY ATTENTION TO
INTERNALS AND THE INTERNALS
WHIPS ON ME IN BOTH DIRECTIONS
DON'T LISTEN TO ME ABOUT THAT.
I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT TO POINT
OUT WHERE THE WEAKNESS IS NOW
BECAUSE IT'S NOT THAT BIG OF A
DEAL
TRANSPORTS ARE DOWN 11 DAYS IN A
ROW.
THAT'S THE LONGEST STREAKS
YOU'VE SEEN THEM DOWN IN 40%
THEY ARE ONLY DOWN 6% OVERALL.
IT'S PERSISTENT SELLING BUT IT'S
NICKELS AND DIMES.
IT'S NOT HUGE DAMAGE
I KNOW A WILL THE OF PEOPLE
TALKING ABOUT THAT
THEY START WITH THE DOWN THEORY
STUFF.
I'M GOING TO HOLD OFF THAT
BIGGER PICTURE
SOME BOTTOMING ACTION IN THE
FAANG NAMES.
IT HAD NOT BEEN A LEADER THIS
YEAR
THEY TAKE UP BIG REAL ESTATE
THE ACCUSED ARE BEING BOUGHT ALL
MORNING.
COMBINE THAT WITH XPI.
SMH, THE SEMIS, FINDING SOME
SUPPORT.
MAYBE THIS WEEK IS WHAT YOU
NEEDED TO BE A PART OF THAT
REFRESHES.
>> ALL OF THAT WHAT YOU LAID OUT
TRUMPS THE TRANSPORT PAINING,
THE RUSSELL.
>> THAT'S A WHIPY AVERAGE.
THE TRANSPORTS DO NOT BEHAVE THE
WAY THE INDUSTRIALS DO
IT'S WAY LESS STOCKS
IT'S SMALLER COMPANIES
IT'S AIRLINES THAT TRADE BASED
ON NOTHING
IT'S IMPORTANT NOT TO OVERSTATE.
>> FORGET THE TRANSPORTS
WHAT ABOUT THE RUSSELL
WEAKNESS IN THE RUSSELL.
SMALL CAPS LEAD YOU DOWN
THEY LEAD YOU UP
>> THEY ARE THINLY TRADED.
>> ALMOST ALL THE RETURNS FROM
EVERY MAJOR INDEX BUT ALL THE
SIZE SPECK TRUCKSTRUMS HAVE COMM
MULTIPLE EXPANSIONS.
IT'S BEEN THE REDUCTION IN THE
TRADE TENSION.
ALSO BIT OF A PAUSE IN GROWTH
CONCERNS
SMALL CAPSSENSITIVE.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU CAN DENY
THE FACT THE ECONOMY HAS SLOWED
AND THAT'S GOT TO CONTINUE
IN TERMS OF INCREASING HAS NO
IMPACT ON THE ECONOMY EFFORT
>> IT'S A PERFECT TIME TO HAVE
THE CONVERSATION ABOUT THE BULL
MARKET
OUR NEXT GUEST HAD A FRONT ROW
SEAT TO THE BEGINNING OF THE
RUN.
BOB DIAMOND.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU
>> FLNICE TO BE HERE.
>> THIS WEEKEND WE'RE MARKING A
DECADE OF THE BULL MARKET.
THE BOTTOM CALLED BY OUR FORMER
COLLEAGUE.
LET'S REVISIT THAT MOMENT AND
THEN WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT ON THE
OTHER SIDE
>> I'M GOING TO STEP OUT ON A
LIMB
I THINK WE'RE AT A BOTTOM.
>> HE WAS RIGHT.
THE QUESTION IS DO YOU THINK
WE'RE CLOSER TO THE END OF THIS
DECADE LONG BULL RUN
>> THERE'S NO EASY ANSWER TO
THAT
I HAVE TO GO BACK TO MARK'S
COMMENT.
I WAS NOWHERE OPTIMISTIC AS HE
WAS AT THAT MOMENT
I THINK IT'S HARD TO OVER STATE
HOW DEEP AND HOW DARK THAT
CORRECTION WAS
PROBABLY THE MOST SEVERE OF ANY
CORRECTION SINCE THE SECOND
WORLD WAR.
I THINK THE S&P WAS DOWN
SOMETHING LIKE 60% FROM PEAK TO
TROUGH IN A THREE OR FOUR MONTH
PERIOD
I THINK FUNDING FOR FINANCIAL
INSTITUTIONS WAS REALLY, REALLY
CHALLENGED AROUND THE WORLD.
TO THINK WE'RE UP NOW WITH A
STRONG PRIVATE SECTOR IN THE
U.S. AS WE HAVE.
I THINK IT'S A BIT OF TWO
STORIES, SCOTT
IN THE SHORT TO MEDIUM TERM,
IT'S HARD NOT TO BE IMPRESSED.
MY OWN VIEW IS BY THE SECOND
HALF OF THIS YEAR WE'LL BE
RAISING RATES AGAIN IN THE U.S
ON THE OTHER HAND THERE'S SOME
REAL STORM WARNINGS OUT THERE
AROUND CREDIT.
>> IT'S AN INTERESTING POINT OF
VIEW
THE PREVAILING VIEW IS CUT
BECAUSE THINGS ARE DICEY.
>> I THINK THE VERY, VERY FAST
ACTION OF THE GOVERNOR IS VERY,
VERY IMPORTANT
I THINK A LOT OF THE POSITIVES
THAT I'M MENTIONING ABOUT THE
U.S. PRIVATE SECTOR, I WOULDN'T
BE SAYING ABOUT EUROPE
I THINK EUROPE HAD MORE GROWTH
CHALLENGES
I THINK THE FACT THAT GOVERNOR
MOVED AS QUICKLY AS HE DID TO
SAY WE'RE GOING TO DO WHAT WE DO
AGAIN ACROSS EUROPE IS VERY
IMPORTANT.
>> YOU WORRIED ABOUT THE
EUROPEAN BANKS
>> HOW CAN ONE NOT BE WORRIED?
WE'RE INVESTING IN EUROPEAN
BANKS WHERE WE CAN FIND
PLATFORMS WITHOUT NON-PERFORMING
LOANS, WITHOUT LEGACY TECHNOLOGY
WHERE WE CAN GET BUSINESSES INTO
THE ECONOMY.
IF YOU LOOK AT GREECE AS A GOOD
EXAMPLE.
WE HAVE A BANK THERE WHICH IS A
CHALLENGER BANK.
IT HAS NO NON-PERFORMING LOANS
IF YOU LOOK AT THE FOUR SYSTEMIC
BANKS.
THE 25 BANKS IN GREECE TEN YEARS
AGO ARE NOW FOUR
THE NON-PERFORMING LOANS IN
THOSE FOUR BANKS ARE OVER 640%
AND WE'RE TEN YEARS ON FROM THE
CRISIS
HOW CAN ONE NOT BE WORRIED PBT.
>> GREATEST MISTAKE OF ALL TIME
WAS FOR THE EUROPEAN BANKS NOT
TO RECAPITALIZE AND IN SOME WAYS
THEY HAVEN'T TAKEN THEIR FULL
DOSAGE OF MEDICINE TO THIS DAY
>> WHAT A GREAT LESSON
IF YOU LOOK BACK TEN YEARS, YOU
LOOK AT BANK AMERICA AND CITI,
BOTH WERE CLOSE TO INSOLVING
YOU'RE ALL TAKING EQUITY
NO STIGMA.
YOU CAN'T PAY THAT BACK TO THE
GOFRT UNT
GOVERNMENT UNTIL YOU PASS THE
STRESS TEST.
TEN YEARS ON, WE HAVE A VERY
STRONG FINANCIAL SYSTEM IN THE
U.S. AND CITI AND B OF A ARE
THRIVING
WE HAVE THE ISSUES WITH ROYAL
BANK OF SCOTLAND STILL ACROSS
EUROPE
IT'S A GREAT LESSON.
>> DO YOU THINK IN HIENDS SIGHT
SOMETHING THAT WENT LITTLE
REMARK AT THE TIME BUT WHAT
MIGHT HAVE BEEN THE PROXIMATE
CAUSE AT THE BOTTOM YOU ALSO HAD
THE SUSPENSION OF MARKED
ACCOUNTING
THEY SAID THE BANKS NO LONGER
HAVE TO CALL ALL OF THIS A LOSS.
THEY HAVE MORE TIME NOW AND THAT
SEEMS TO HAVE COINCIDED WITH THE
BANKS -- THE SHARE PRICES OF THE
BANKS NOT GOING DOWN
DO YOU THINK THAT WAS REALLY
IMPORTANT COMPONENT AND SHOULD
THAT BE A POLICY TOOL GOING
FORWARD FOR FINANCIAL CRISIS
>> I THINK IT WAS FAR MORE
IMPORTANT AT THE TIME, TO BE
HONEST
WE NEED TO FIX THE SYSTEM.
WE'RE NOT GOING HAVE AN KPLI
WITHOUT -- ECONOMY WITHOUT A
THR
THRIVING SYSTEM.
I THINK THE U.S. LED THE WAY AND
TODAY YOU CAN SEE THE CLEAR
DIFFERENCES.
>> YOU LOOK BACK AT THAT PERIOD
AND YOU SAY, AND MANY DO, THEY
SAVED THE WORLD.
HOW DO YOU THINK POWELL ARE
HANDLING THINGS TODAY?
HE'S A DIFFERENT KIND OF CENTRAL
BANK
THEY MADE THIS GREAT PIVOT
ARE THEY ON THE RIGHT PATH
>> IN MY VIEW, NOT WITH STANDING
THINGS I SAID ABOUT THE PRIVATE
SECTOR, IT SLCLEARLY SLOWED DOW.
I THINK CHAIRMAN POWELL
RESPONDED TO THAT.
I ALSO THINK THAT CHAIRMAN
POWELL BELIEVES IF WE DON'T GET
BA
BACK TO A MORE NORMALIZED
INDUSTRY, WE WON'T
IF WE DON'T THE NEXT CHALLENGE
COMES, WE'RE TEN YEARS ON.
KEEP IN MIND WE SPENT $2
TRILLION ON TAX AND SPENDING
WE HAVE KIND OF WIPED OUT THE
FISCAL RESPONSE THAT WE CAN HAVE
AND WE'RE STILL NOT WHERE WE
NEED TO BE TO HAVE MONETARY
TOOLS.
THE QUESTION WE HAVE TO ASK
OURSELVES IS HOW REPAIRED ARE WE
FOR THE NEXT CHANCE?
>> YOU SEE EVERY TIME POWELL OR
SOMEBODY TALKS ABOUT THE HIGH
RATE AND PRE-PIVOT, THE MARKET
GETS MOTION SICKNESS ANY TIME
THERE'S A THOUGHT OF RAISING
RATES.
NOW YOU HAVE THE PIVOT
YOU THINK THE FED IS TOO
BEHOLDEN TO THE STOCK MARKET
>> I THINK THE FED IS
INDEPENDENT.
I THINK THE ACTIONS IN THE
FOURTH QUARTER, I'M COMFORTABLE
WITH
>> WOULD YOU SAY LIKE GERMAN
FACTORY ORDERS WERE DOWN,
EXPECTED TO BE UP A LITTLE
THIS WAS A HUGE WIPE OUT FOR THE
GERMAN SECTOR.
PERHAPS ONE OF THE REASONS THEY
GOT PUT IN DAYS AGO IS BECAUSE
MAYBE THEY KNEW A BIT ABOUT THIS
DATA AHEAD OF THAT
IF EUROPE IS SLOWING TO THE
POINT WHERE YOU'VE GOT FACTORY
PRODUCTION DOWN THAT MUCH AT THE
BIGGEST DRIVER IN EUROPE,
GERMANY, WOULDN'T YOU SAY IT
WILL BE DIFFICULT MOVING UP ON
RATES WHEN THEY ARE PUSHING DOWN
SO HARD ON THEIR SIDE AND LIKELY
TO PRESS DOWN HARDER GOING
FOR
FORWARD?
>> OF COURSE IT'S MORE CHANCING.
IT WOULD BE WONDERFUL IF THE
GLOBAL ECONOMY WAS ALL GROWING
TOGETHER
HERE IN THE U.S. WE DO HAVE A
BETTER CHAGS
WE HAVE A STRONGER PRIVATE
SECTOR
I THINK WE'LL HAVE TO GET BACK
TO RAISING RATES EVENTUALLY.
THE QUESTION IS ONE OF TIMING.
COMING BACK TO EUROPE, MY
CONCERN IS A BIT DIFFERENT
I HAPPEN TO BE A HUGE FAN.
WE'RE TEN YEAR ANNIVERSARY
TEN YEARS AGO, THEY RAISED
RATES.
>> THEY HAD TO REVERSE THAT IN
>> EXACTLY
THE END OF 2011, THE GOVERNOR
DID THE FIRST TERM REPO
OPERATION.
THAT WASN'T THE TIME
WE WERE WAKING UP IN THE MORNING
AND THINKING ABOUT SOME OF THE
LARGER EUROPEAN BANKS BEING
INSOLVENT.
HE TOOK INSOLVENCY OFF THE
TABLE.
THAT HAS ALLOWED SOME RECOVERY
THE REAL CHALLENGE IS, OCTOBER,
HIS TERM RUNS OUT.
I THINK IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT
THAT WE SEE A GOVERNOR OF ECB
RESPECTED BY THE MARKETS BUT
ALSO WHO RESPECTS THE MARKET
>> THEY'VE GOT OTHER ISSUES.
>> VERY STRONG UNDERLYING
ECONOMY.
VERY STRONG BUSINESS
IT'S A VERY ENTREPRENEURIAL.
>> DOESN'T POWELL RISK FALLING
INTO THE SAME TRAP IF RATES ARE
STILL MOVING LOWER IN EUROPE BY
VIRTUE OF WHAT WAS SAID
YESTERDAY.
HOW CAN THE FED GET BACK ON THE
PATH OF RAISING RATES WHILE THE
REST OF THE WORLD IS GOING DOWN
IF NOT STILL NEGATIVE.
>> IF THE U.S. ECONOMY PROVES
STRENGTHS, 3.8% UNEMPLOYMENT IS
PRETTY STRONG POSITION TO BE IN.
IF WE SEE A RECOVERY AND
STRENGTH NOT WITH STANDING
WHAT'S HAPPENING IN EUROPE, I
BELIEVE GOVERNOR POWELL WILL
MOVER BACK
WE STILL HAVE 4 TRILLION IN
SATES.
IF WE DON'T BUY ANOTHER SECURITY
AND WE LET EVERYTHING WE DEEM,
BY THE END OF THIS YEAR WE STILL
HAVE THREE AND A HALF TRILLION
WE ALSO HAVE, THIS IS THE STORM
WARNINGS, SCOTT, THAT I WORRY
ABOUT.
WE HAVE MORE BELOW INVESTMENT
GRADE DEBT AND MORE LEVERAGE
ENDING OUTSTANDING ABOUT 4
TRILLION THAN WE EVER HAD
BEFORE
>> I DEFINITELY DON'T THINK THAT
POWELL WANTS TO BE ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF HISTORY.
I THINK THAT PATIENT DATA
DEPENDENCE IS LIKELY WHAT THEY
WILL CONTINUE WITH
I'M CURIOUS TO YOUR THOUGHTS IN
BANKING INDUSTRY
WHAT IS YOUR THOUGHT ON COMMERCE
AND WE HAVE SEEN WHAT'S GOING ON
THERE.
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS ABOUT THE
CONSOLIDATION ACROSS EUROPE AND
VERY SPECIFICALLY WITH DEUTSCHE
P.
>> MAYBE IT'S A SECOND STAGE AND
VERY SELECTIVE
THOSE 25, ARE THOSE FOUR, IT WAS
A FORCED CONSOLIDATION
I WOULD EXPECT TO SEE A COMMERCE
BANK, DEUTSCHE BANK.
IT SEEMS CONVENIENT FOR GERMANY.
>> DO YOU ASCRIBE THAT THERE
DIDN'T SEEM TO BE CONSEQUENCES
FROM THE PEOPLE AT THE HEAD OF
THESE LARGE INSTITUTIONS AND HAS
RISK TAKING THAT TLLED TO A LOTO
CRISIS
DO YOU THINK THAT 5 OR 10% OF
ANGER IN OUR POLITICAL SYSTEM
ESPECIALLY AMONG YOUNGER PEOPLE,
DO YOU THINK THAT'S COME FING FM
THE EVENTS YEARS AGO
>> I THINK THERE'S ANGER IN THIS
COUNTRY.
I THINK THERE'S MORE ANGER IN
EUROPE AND UK TOWARD BANKS AND
BANKERS AND PLACING BLAME.
I THINK THAT'S PART OF WHAT
YOU'RE SEEING.
>> YOU CAN SEE THE SEEDS BEING
SEWN AS PART OF THE INCOME
INEQUALITY ISSUE OVER THE LAST
DECADE
PEOPLE WHO ARE INVESTED IN THE
MARKET HAVE OBVIOUSLY DONE
INCREDIBLY WELL OVER THE LAST
TEN YEARS.
PEOPLE WHO LOST THEIR SHIRTS AND
AFRAID TO GET BACK IN AND WEALTH
DESTRUCTION.
YESTERDAY WE HAD THIS NUMBER
COME OUT, THIS TREMENDOUS NUMBER
OF WEALTH DESTRUCTION AT THE END
OF THE YEAR RIVALLED ONLY BY
IT WAS A MARKABLE PERIOD OF
TIME
IT SPEAKS TO HOW FAR WE HAVE
COME AND HOW FAR SOME OF US HAVE
TO GO.
>> I THINK I LIKE TO KEEP COMING
BACK TO THE POINT ABOUT IT WAS
THE SYSTEM
IT WAS FINANCIAL SERVICES.
THE TRUTH IS TODAY, TEN YEARS
ON, BANKS IN EUROPE AND THE U.S.
ARE SAFER AND SOUNDER.
THERE'S NO QUESTION ABOUT THAT
THE QUESTION IS OR AT THE TIME,
THE QUESTION IS THE U.S. ACTIONS
IN TERMS OF BEING FOCUSED ON
REPAIRING THE SYSTEM WERE FAR
MORE BENEFICIAL TO THE ECONOMY
AND THE U.S. THAN THE ACTIONS
TAKEN IN EUROPE.
THERE'S A LESSON THERE
>> YOU STILL HAVE SOME CONCERNS
WITH ISSUES WITHIN THE FINANCIAL
SERVICES INDUSTRY, HOWEVER,
YOU'RE ON THE PROWL.
>> IF YOU THINK ABOUT THE STOCK
MARKET, S&P UP FOUR TIMES OR
FIVE TIMES SINCE 2009.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT PRIVATE SECT AS
A WHOLE, PEOPLE WORRY ABOUT
VALUATIONS AND WORRY ABOUT THE
HIGHER COST OF DEBT.
VALUATIONS IN MOST SECTORS ARE
UP FIVE OR SIX TIMES AND THE
COST OF LEVERAGE IS HIGHER
IN FINANCIAL SFERVICES WE'RE
BELOW THE LEVELS OF 2008 AND
IT'S WHERE THEY BENEFIT THE
OPERATIONS OF THE BUSINESS
THE HIGHER COST OF THE INTEREST
RATE AND WE LOVE THE SECTOR.
WHAT'S RANGED IS A RESULT OF
FINANCIAL CRISIS IS WITH THE
HIGHER BUFFER UPON BUFFER OF
CAPITAL FOR THE LARGER CONNECTED
GLOBAL BANKS WHERE WE HAD DECADE
AFTER DECADE OF GLOBAL, GLOBAL,
GLO
GLOBAL, BIG, BIG, BIG.
IT'S REALLY THE MODEL OF BEING
NATIONAL OR REGIONAL AND BEING
FOCUSED AND SELECTED ABOUT WHAT
YOU'RE DOING.
WITH A GROUP OF PEOPLE WE
INVESTED 25% WHICH IS REALLY THE
BACKBONE FOR THE 401(k) PLANS
AND THE 920 PLANS.
IT'S NOT NOT VERY SEXY PART BUT
WE LOVE THAT SECTOR.
>> THERE'S STILL A RESIDUAL FEAR
OF WHAT HAPPENED IN FINANCIAL
SERVICES BUT THERE'S ALSO AN
OPAQUENESS THAT PEOPLE NEED TO
UNDERSTAND WHICH IS WHY WHEN
WE'RE DOING THIS IN THE PRIVATE
SECTOR VERSUS THE PUBLIC, IT'S
EASIER TO GET INVOLVED
>> IF I TOLD YOU AS WE MARK THE
TENth ANNIVERSARY OF THE BULL
MARKET THIS WEEKEND, IF I TOLD
YOU ON MARCH 9th OF '09, WE'RE
ABOUT TO EMBARK ON THIS LONGEST
BULL MARKET ON RECORD, YOU'D
HAVE SAID WHAT
>> YOU'RE CRAZY.
>> I FIGURED YOU'LL SAY THAT
>> I DIDN'T GET THAT RIGHT, FOR
SURE
>> IT'S BEEN GREAT HAVING YOU.
THANKS FOR SITTING WITH US
>> THANK YOU
>>> HERE'S WHAT'S COMING UP ON
THE HALFTIME REPORT.
>> STRAIGHT AHEAD, THE ANALYSTS
GOING THE OTHER WAY ON NETFLIX
SEE WHY HE IS SAYING IT'S TIME
TO COOL OFF WHEN IT COMES TO
THIS HIGH FLYING STUFF
THE CALL OF THE DAY IS NEXT.
>>> BEFORE THE BREAK, OUR DATA
PARTNERS AT KENSHO ON WHAT
HAPPENS AFTER THE XLE ENERGY ETF
DROPS 4% IN A WEEK
THE NUMBER SHOWS IT TRADE
POSITIVE 76% OF THE TIME A WEEK
LATER.
UP 156%.
FOR MORE TWO TO CNBC.COM/KENSHO.
THE HALFTIME REPORT IS BACK IN
TWO MINUTES.
CME Group can help you navigate
risks
and capture opportunities.
We enable you to reach global
markets
and drive forward with broader
possibilities.
CME Group - How the world
advances.
♪
You always pay your
insurance on time.
Tap one little bumper
and up go your rates.
What good is having insurance if
you get punished for using it?
News flash: nobody's perfect.
For drivers with
Accident Forgiveness,
Liberty Mutual won't
raise your rates
due to your first accident.
Switch and you could save $782
on Home and Auto insurance.
Call for a free quote today.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>>> SHARES OF NETFLIX SOARING
NEARLY 50% OFF THEIR LOWS.
BUCKINGHAM SAYS TIME TO MOVER TO
THE SIDELINES.
THEY KEEP THE PRICE TARGET AT
382.
THEY SAY IT'S NOT COMPELLING
IT'S AN INTERESTING NOTE
THEY TALK ABOUT SENSITIVITY TO
ANY MARKET PULL BACK
NEW COMPETITION AND MARKET
VOLATILITY THAT'S LIKELY TO
CONTINUE RELATIVE TO DCHINA AND
THE TRADE FIGHT.
IS NOW THE TIME TO GET OUT AFTER
50% JUMP
>> I DON'T THINK COMPETITION IS
THE REASON TO GET OUT OF IT.
I DON'T AGREE WITH THAT ONE AT
ALL.
FOR YOU TO BUILD A CRIMINAL MASS
TO COMPETE WITH THESE GUYS, I'M
NOT GOING TO USE THE HACK PHRASE
MOTE BUT I'LL SAY FOR SOMEBODY
TO BUILD A CRIMINAL MASS THAT
THEY CAN SUSTAIN EVEN IF IT'S
DI
DISNEY, I'M GOING TO BE SHOCKED
IF THEY DO IT.
I JUST DON'T SEE IT.
>> YOU DON'T SEE AMAZON PRIME
BEING WILLING TO SPEND BILLIONS
OF DOLLARS EVERY YEAR TO MAKE
SHOWS AS GOOD AS NETFLIX OR
BETTER PLUS ACQUIRING SPORTS
RIGHTS
YOU DON'T SEE AT&T NOW OWNING
HBO AND PUSHING BILLIONS OF
DOLLARS AT NEW CONTENT
>> NO.
>> YOU DON'T SEE DISNEY
LAUNCHING IN FOURTH QUARTER OF
THIS YEAR WITH EVERY DISNEY
TITLE IN HISTORY PLUS NEW SHOWS
THAT DON'T EXIST
>> ALL OF THOSE GUYS --
>> THEY'VE NEVER BEEN THIS
COMMITTED.
>> THEY'VE ALSO NEVER DONE IT
BEFORE
SGR T
>> THERE'S AN HBO APP NOW.
>> DO YOU KNOW HOW MANY
SUBSCRIBERS THEY HAVE?
>> TEN S OF MILLIONS.
>> NO, NO.
>> MORE AND MORE PEOPLE ARE
DROPPING CABLE
>> HBO WILL BE PUSH ED
THEY WERE MAKING LIKE TEN SHOWS
A YEAR
>> LET'S LOOK AT THIS A LITTLE
BIT DIFFERENTLY.
IF YOU OWN IT, THE QUESTION IS
DO YOU SELL IT
>> WE'RE IN GAME OF THRONES
TERRITORY.
>> IF YOU DON'T OWN IT, DO YOU
BUY IT
>> CAN WE PUT UP A CHART
>> THE COMPETITIVE ISSUES ARE
WO
WORTHY
SG WHO IS HBO GOING TO TAKE
MARKET SHARE FROM.
THESE GUYS ARE GOING TO EAT EACH
OTHER.
NETFLIX GETS TO SIT BACK LIKE
THIS GUY AND LET THEM DESTROY
EACH OTHER
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE
>> THEY'VE GOT TO GRAB A
CRITICAL MASS.
THEY CANNOT DO IT.
>> WHEN YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
GROWTH, STOCK TRADES ON
SUBSCRIBER GROWTH.
>> MAYBE THEY DON'T TAKE SHARE
FROM NETFLIX
>> WITH AMAZON'S ABILITY TO CUT
PRICES
>> NETFLIX IS RAISING AND PEOPLE
ARE STILL STAYING THERE.
I DON'T DISAGREE THEY WILL BUILD
OUT BUT FOR NOW.
>> THE CONTENT IS THE SAME FOR
THE COMPETITORS.
>> ONE AT A TIME DOC, AND THAT
ONE IS ME.
>> THE THING IN MY EAR IS LIKE
BUZZING.
>> I AGREE
>> WE HAVE A 395 PRICE TARGET ON
IT
>> KATE MOORE, FACEBOOK, AMAZON,
HALF THE FAANGS RIGHT THERE.
DOES THE MARKET NEED IT MORE
>> THERE HAS TO BE A LOT OF
INVESTMENT INTO CONTEXT.
COMPETITION IS HEATING UP ACROSS
THE WORLD.
SOME OF THAT IS BECAUSE OF THE
CYCLICAL PARTS OF THE SECTOR
THERE'S A LOT OF PLACES WE THINK
RECURRING REVENUE WILL HOLD
THROUGH DESPITE ANY ECONOMIC
UNCERTAINTY IN ANY SORT OF LIKE
GEO POLITICAL RISK
I DON'T KNOW
WE STAY CONSTRUCTIVE
I CAN'T TALK INDIVIDUAL NAMES ON
AIR.
>> LET'S LEAVE THAT THERE.
LET'S GO TO SUE.
>>> HERE IS WHAT'S HAPPENING
PRESIDENT TRUMP TALKING TO
REPORTERS AS HE DEPARTED FROM
THE WHITE HOUSE FOR HIS TRIP TO
ALABA
ALABAMA.
COMMENTING ON THE 47 MONTH
SENTENCE FOR PAUL MANAFORT
>> I FEEL VERY BADLY FOR PAUL
MANAFORT
I THINK IT'S BEEN A VERY TOUGH
TIME FOR HIM, BUT IF YOU NOTICE
BOTH HIS LAWYER, A HIGHLY
RESPECTED MAN AND A VERY HIGHLY
RESPECTED JUDGE.
THE JUDGE SAID THERE WAS NO
COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA.
>> FORMER ARMY INTELLIGENCE
ANALYST CHELSEA MANNING HAS BEEN
JAILED FOR REFUSING TO TESTIFY
TO A GRAND JURY INVESTIGATING
WIKILEAKS.
HE TOLD THE JUDGE SHE WILL
QUOTE, ACCEPT WHATEVER YOU BRING
UPON ME, END QUOTE
>>> MORE THAN TWO DOZEN TOP
WOMEN SOCCER PLAYERS SUING THE
U.S. AND NATIONAL SOCCER
FEDERATION CLAIMING THE
ORGANIZATION PAYS THEM LESS THAN
MALE PLAYERS AND DENIES THEM
EQUAL RAVEL, TRAINING AND
CONDITIONS
COMES THREE MONTHS BEFORE THEY
HAVE TO DEFEND THEIR WORLD CUP
TITLE.
BACK TO YOU.
>> THEY'RE STILL DEBATING THE
N
NETFLIX.
>> I BET THEY ARE.
>>> S&P IS DOWN 20.5
TRYING TO STAY OFF THE BOTTOM.
HALF TIME IS BACK RIGHT AFTER
THIS
The future of
technology investing
lies beyond the
tech sector.
It's about technology
transforming every sector.
♪
At PGIM,
our bottom-up approach
uses a technology lens
to identify
long-term winners.
From energy...
to real estate...
to retail.
Finding such
opportunities for alpha
is the true value
of active investing.
And around the world,
you have a partner
in that pursuit.
PGIM:
The Global Investment Management
Businesses of Prudential.
REBEKKAH:
Opioids has taken everything
The Global Investment Management
and everyone I've ever
loved away from me.
Everything.
I blew my ankle out
and I got prescribed pain
pills by my doctor.
If making my detox public
is gonna help somebody
I'm all for it.
I just wish I would've
had a warning.
(Baby crying)
♪♪
♪Hold on, I'm comin'♪
♪Hold On
Don't you worry,♪
♪I'm comin'♪
♪Here we come,
Hold on♪
♪We're about to save you
I'm comin', yeah♪
♪Hold On
Don't you worry,♪
♪I'm comin'♪
>>> THE SHARES OF CLEVELAND
CLIFFS FALLING TODAY
TRADERS BETTING IT WILL TURN
AROUND AND PERHAPS SOON BASED ON
OPTIONS BAACTIVITY THAT JON IS
SEEING
>> THEY'RE NOT LOOKING FOR A
HUGE JUMP TO THE UPSIDE.
IT'S A RELATIVELY MODEST
THEY'RE BUYING APRIL
THAT'S WHERE MONEY CAME IN RIGHT
AWAY TODAY
THEY CAME IN BUYING THOSE CALLS.
OCTOBER 10 CALLS THEY BOUGHT
NEARLY 4,000 RIGHT AWAY.
I LIKE THE TRADE BECAUSE IT'S
ALREADY EASED BACK
I'LL PROBABLY BE IN THESE
OCTOBER CALLS MAYBE TWO MONTHS
ANOTHER QUICK ONE, THIS IS SWISS
INDUSTRIAL COMPANY, ABB.
THIS ONE WE SAW PRETTY STRONG
ACTIVITY AGAIN WITH THE WEAKER
MARKET LIKE THE ENTRY POINT
WE'RE GETTING HERE TODAY
THESE ARE THE APRIL OPTIONS IN
THIS ONE, JUDGE.
WITH THIS ONE, TRADIE ING $18.80
THEY CAME IN BY THE 19 CALL.
JUST OUT OF MONEY IN BOTH CASES.
I LIKED THIS ONE
I BOUGHT THESE
ABOUT 3500 TRADED.
I'LL PROBABLY BE IN THESE 30
DAYS GIVE OR TAKE.
>> COME ON BACK OVER
>> THANKS VERY MUCH.
>>> VIEWER QUESTIONS COMING IN
WE'LL GET TO THAT, NEXT.
YOU DO STILL HAVE TIME TO REACH
US AS WELL ON CNBC.COM/HALFTIME
OR TWEET US.
WE'RE BACK THIS TWO MINUTES.
You're searching
for something more...
...red-blooded.
Right this way.
You thirst for adrenaline,
you hunger for raw power.
Well, you've come
to the right place.
The road is yours, dig in.
♪♪
You should be mad they gave this
guy a promotion.
You should be mad at
forced camaraderie.
And you should be mad at tech
that makes things worse.
But you're not mad,
because you have E*TRADE,
who's tech makes life easier
by automatically adding
technical patterns on charts
and helping you understand what
they mean.
Don't get mad.
Get E*TRADE's simplified
technical analysis.
Your insurance rates skyrocket
after a scratch so small
you could fix it with a pen.
How about using that pen to sign
up for new insurance instead?
For drivers with
Accident Forgiveness,
Liberty Mutual won't
raise their rates
because of their
first accident.
Switch and you could save $782
on Home and Auto insurance.
Call for a free quote today.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>>> LET'S ANSWER SOME OF YOUR
QUESTIONS.
FROM CHUCK IN MISSISSIPPI.
THANK YOU CHUCK FOR THE
QUESTION
SHOULD I HOLD OR SELL THEM NOW
WHAT SHOULD HE DO?
>> FIRST IS THE CAVEAT
IF IT'S LONG TERM, HOLD ONTO IT.
SHORT TERM, I THINK THERE'S
WEAKNESS
THE STOCKS HAVE HAD A HUGE MOVE.
I DON'T THINK THE ENVIRONMENT IS
GREAT FOR THEM
I THINK THERE'S WAY TOO MUCH
OPTIMISM
>> VICTOR IN NEW YORK, FOR YOU
JON.
ANYONE SIGH IT TOPPING 60 BUCKS
BY THE SUMMER.
>> YOU'LL GET TWO BIG CHANCES,
TWO BIG CATALYSTS THAT ARE OUT
THERE IN THE FUTURE.
ONE IS THE OPEC MEETING IN
APRIL.
THE OTHER IS JUNE.
THEY'RE NOT EXPECTED TO RAISE IN
APRIL.
THEY ARE PERHAPS MOVING TOWARDS
THAT IN JUNE
I WOULD SAY TIME FRAME, JUNE FOR
YOU AS FAR AS THE CATALYST, I
LIKE THAT.
>> TRB, YOUR TURN.
KEN IN ISCONSIN.
BROADCOM
>> THE UP TREND IS STILL IN
TACT
I WOULD HAVE A STOP HERE
255, 260 AREA SEEMS TO BE THE
FORMER RESISTANCE.
IF YOU WANT KNOW WHERE TO MANAGE
YOUR RISK, THAT'S WHERE I WOULD
PUT IN TRAIL
IF YOU'RE WRONG, YOU'LL FIND
THAT QUICKLY
>> KATE.
WITH THE ECB MOVE, WHERE DO YOU
SEE EEM GOING?
>> WE'RE PRETTY CONSTRUCTIVE ON
EMERGING MARKETS
I WILL SAY THAT OVERALL DOV
DOVISHNESS FROM THE FED AND ECB
LAYS THE GROUND WORK TO
STIMULATE.
THIS IS PRETTY GOOD FOR ASSETS
WE SEE A LOT OF UPSIDE IN TERMS
OF EARNINGS GROWTH AS WELL AS
GDP GROWTH
>> GOOD STUFF.
>>> UP NEXT, WE HAVE SOMEONE
ELSE TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTIONS.
HE'S A MEMBER OF CNBC'S
FINANCIAL WELLNESS ADVISORY
COUNSEL.
HE'S A FORMER NEW YORK YANKEE,
WORLD SERIES CHAMPION.
HE'S HERE TO SIT WITH US
HE'LL SHARE HIS INVESTMENT
STRATEGY
SEND US YOUR QUESTIONS
YOU CAN TWEET US AT HALFTIME
REPORT
USE THE HASHTAG ASK HALFTIME
MACHIN
issues facing our world,
what do you see?
We see breakthrough medicines
getting to patients
in record time.
We see harnessing natural gas
unleashing the promise
of clean energy.
We see engineers simulating
the future to improve today.
At Emerson,
when issues become inspiration,
focusing core strengths
to create a better world
isn't just a result,
it's a responsibility.
Emerson.
Consider It Solved.
So, ServiceNow put your
workflows in the cloud, huh?
Mmhm.
Your employees must love you.
[ chuckles ]
Thank you.
You could say that.
I love you.
ServiceNow works for you.
Opportunities aren't always
obvious.
Sometimes, they just drop in.
CME Group can help you navigate
risks
and capture opportunities.
We enable you to reach global
markets
and drive forward with broader
possibilities.
CME Group - How the world
advances.
♪
.
>>> WELCOME BACK
COMING UP, THE CHAIRMAN WILL
JOIN US TO DISCUSS INVESTORS
GETTING ACCESS IN OTHER WORDS TO
GET ACCESS LIKE BIGGER FORMS
>>> THE FINANCIAL TRANSACTION
TAX PLUS ON TODAY'S RAPID FIRE,
ONE CEO IS BLAMING INJUSTICE FOR
THE COMPANY'S DISAPPOINTING
QUARTERLY RESULTS.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
TO LA CROIX.
WE'LL SEE YOU AT THE TOP OF THE
HOUR
BACK THE YOU
>>> ALL RIGHT.
WELCOME BACK TO THE HALFTIME
REPORT
CNBC MADE AN INITIATE IVE CA ED
INVEST IN YOU, GROW.
WE'RE HONORED THAT MARK WILL BE
PART OF OUR CNBC WELLNESS
ADVISORY YOU
PART OF A GOOD GROUP
SOME OTHER BIG NAMES
FINANCIAL LITERACY HAS BEEN A
BIG PART OF YOUR LIFE.
>> WE HEAR THESE STORIES ABOUT
ATHLETES GOING BROKE
THERE'S SOME SIMPLE REASONS FOR
THAT
YOU KNOW, ONE OF THE GREAT
THINGS THAT CNBC HAS ALLOWED ME
TO DO IS TO BE ON SHOWS LIKE
THIS AND TALK TO DIFFERENT
ATHLETES AND REALLY EVERY DAY
AMERICANS ABOUT SAVING AND
MAKING THE RIGHT DECISIONS
>> BETWEEN ONE AND TEN WHAT
NUMBER WOULD YOU SAY IS THE
LEVEL OF FINANCIAL LITERACY IN
PROFESSIONAL SPORTS AMONG THE
ATHLETES
>> IT'S PROBABLY A THREE OR
FOUR, UNFORTUNATELY.
>> THAT LOW?
>> YOU HAVE TO BE SO FOCUS ODD
PLAY YOUR SPORT AND IT'S A 12
MONTH A YEAR JOB NO MATTER WHAT
SPORT YOU PLAY
YOU HAVE TO HAVE THAT FOCUS AND
INTENSITY TO DO YOUR JOB ON
FIELD.
YOU TEND NOT TO THINK ABOUT
THINGS OFF THE FIELD
YOU DON'T THINK ABOUT WHEN I'M
40, 50 OR 80 BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO
LIVE IN THE MOMENT
THAT'S THE GREAT THING ABOUT
PROFESSIONAL SPORTS LIVING IN
THE MOMENT
AS ATHLETES WE PLAN TO NOT THINK
AHEAD ENOUGH
>> WERE YOU FINANCIALLY LITERATE
WHEN YOU WERE PLAYING OR IS THIS
A POST-CAREER THING?
>> I HAD SOME GREAT MENTORS
AROUND ME.
MY BAD BEING ONE OF THEM
FIRST THING MY DAD IS LET ME
SHOW YOU WHAT A SPREADSHEET
LOOKS LIKE
LET ME SHOW YOU WHERE YOUR CHECK
IS GOING
WE HAD FINANCIAL ADVISORS IN
BALTIMORE WHEN I FIRST SIGNED BY
PROFESSIONAL CONTRACT.
MOST OF THESE GUYS DON'T START
FROM DAY ONE AND TEN DAERS DOWN
T
-- YEARS DOWN THE ROAD THEY
REALIZE THEY DIDN'T SAVE ENOUGH.
>> I LIKE YOUR MOTTO, THINK OF
THIS IS THE LAST CONTRACT.
YOU GO OUT AND SHOP.
>> YOU ALWAYS THINK THERE'S MORE
MONEY TO COME IN
LISTEN YOU CAN PICK STOCKS FOR
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
PROBABLY UNTIL THE DAY YOU DIE
YOU CAN BE A GOOD STOCK PICKER
I CAN'T BE A GOOD BASEBALL
PLAYER MY ENTIRE LIFE.
A LOT OF GUYS DON'T REALIZE THIS
CONTRACT ON YOUR DESK RIGHT NOW,
THAT COULD BE THE LAST CONTRACT
YOU SIGN
10 MILLION BUCKS YOU BETTER PUT
AWAY 90% OF IT SO YOU CAN LIVE
OFF OF THAT THE REST OF YOUR
LIFE
>> THE PROBLEM OF PREDATORY
ADVISERS OR PEOPLE OUT TO GET A
WEALTHY ONE SOPHISTICATED
INVESTOR THAT'S DATED A LITTLE
BIT AND ONUS IS PUT ON THIS GUY
MAKES BAD DECISIONS OR THIS
GUY'S FAMILY IS TAKINGEING
ADVANTAGE.
LET'S GET PEOPLE EDUCATED SO
THEY CAN MAKE BETTER DECISIONS
ON THEIR OWN AND NOT RELY ON
SHADY FINANCIAL --
>> I AGREE
FINANCIAL ADVISER, IF I HIRE
SOMEBODY, THEY COULD BE BANK OF
AMERICA'S TOP FINANCIAL ADVISER
AND WEALTH MANAGER AND SAY I
WANT TO BUY $5 MILLION BOAT AND
HE GOES MARK WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
YOU DON'T NEED THAT BOAT
YOU'RE FIRED
THESE FINANCIAL ADVISERS ARE
SAYING I DON'T WANT TO MAKE MY
CLIENT UNHAPPY AND IF HE WANTS
TO GO BUY THE BOAT HE'LL BUY THE
BOAT
THAT'S THE PROBLEM
INDIVIDUALS ARE MAKING BAD
DECISIONS.
ADVISERS ARE ADVISING.
THEY DON'T HAVE THE PEN AND
CHECKBOOK TO WRITE THESE CHECKS.
THE PLAYERS ARE THE ONES MAKING
BAD DECISIONS.
>> WHAT'S THE FIRST INVESTMENT
YOU MADE
WHAT'S THE BEST INVESTMENT YOU
MADE
>> THE BEST INVESTMENT I MADE I
BOUGHT A PIECE OF PROPERTY IN
ATLANTA, GEORGIA THAT'S BEING
DEVELOPED AS A BIG MIX USE
DEVELOPMENT IN ATLANTA
I BOUGHT IT BETWEEN 2008 AND
YOU ALL KNOW WHAT HAPPENED TO
THE REAL ESTATE MARKET AT THAT
TIME
I TAUGHT ME ABOUT BUYING LOW
ANY ASSET THERE'S PAR.
BUYING IT LOW AND BUYING AT THE
RIGHT TIME AND PAYING WAY TOO
MUCH FOR IT.
WHAT I LEARNED EARLY IS THERE'S
A BUCKET FOR MY NEST EGG THAT I
PUT AWAY AND I NEVER HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT AGAIN.
THERE'S THE BUCKET FOR
OPPORTUNITIES.
WHEN A PIECE OF PROPERTY COMES
OUT THERE OR THERE'S A COMPANY
THAT YOUR FRIEND, YOU KNOW HE'S
SMART AND FIGURING SOMETHING
OUT, YEAH, I'LL MAKE A BET ON
THAT
BUT I WON'T PUT MY NEST EGG IN
IT
>> YOU TALK ABOUT INVESTING?
>> WE DID.
NOT ENOUGH GUYS TALKED
BECAUSE AT A CERTAIN LEVEL IT
JUST BECOMES NOISE
AND THAT'S WHY I TELL EVERY GUY,
BE BORING IN YOUR INVESTMENTS.
70/30 STOCKS BOND, 60/40
DEPENDING WHERE YOU ARE IN YOUR
LIFE
GET BLUE CHIP STOCKS AND INDEX
FUNDS AND LEAVE THEM ALONE
IF YOU START PICKING STOCKS, YOU
GUYS ARE PROFESSIONALS AND IT'S
TOUGH.
IMAGINE IF I'M A BASEBALL PLAYER
TRYING TO PICK INDIVIDUAL
STOCKS
JUST DOESN'T WORK.
>> I TOLD YOU WE WOULD SOLICIT
QUESTIONS FROM OUR VIEWERS
SCOTT IN PENNSYLVANIA WANTS TO
KNOW WHO OF YOU THREE IS THE
BETTER INVESTOR?
YOU OR JETER OR A-ROD?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THE MOST IN TUNED AND THE ONE
WHO CARES THE MOST SAEKS
-- IS A-ROD.
THIS GUY GETS IT
IT HELPS WHEN YOU HAVE A $250
MILLION CONTRACT AT AGE 26
SOMEBODY GIVES YOU THAT MUCH
MONEY YOU BETTER PAY ATTENTION
ALEX, THIS CONVERSATION WE'RE
HAVING HE'S ONE OF THE GUY THAT
EARLY ON FIGURED IT OUT AND HAS
HAD A LOT OF OPPORTUNITIES
GOT A LOT OF MONEY TO WORK WITH.
HE'S BECOME MORE ATTUNED
INVESTOR
>> HE'S GOTTEN ADVICE FROM
BUFFETT.
JETER BOUGHT THE MARLINS
YOU WANT TO DO SOMETHING LIKE
THAT
>> I DON'T WANT TO BUY A
BASEBALL TEAM.
I HAVE THREE KIDS THAT I LOVE TO
DEATH AND I DON'T WANT TO HAVE A
FULL-TIME JOB.
I LOVE WHAT I'M DOING AT SPEP
AND MY REAL ESTATE PROJECT IN
ATLANTA.
BUT I LOVE SPENDING TIME WITH MY
KIDS
I'M RETIRED.
>> YOU HAVE THAT BASEBALL.
WILL YOU SIGN IT
I'M GOING TO SEND IT TO THE
GENTLEMAN WHOSE QUESTION WE JUST
READ
THANKS
WE APPRECIATE YOU BEING A PART
OF THIS.
HE'S GOING PARTICIPATE AS WELL
IN SOME OF OUR SUMMER
PROGRAMMING FOR FINANCIAL
LITERACY
AN'S COMING UP IN APRIL.
THKS AGAIN
>>> FINAL TRADES ARE NEXT.
Hey, how ya doing? Uh, Phil.
Are you guys good with brakes?
We're OK.
Just OK?
We got a saying here.
If the brakes don't stop it,
something will.
That's not a real saying.
It is around here. I wrote it.
JUST OK IS NOT OK.
Especially when it comes to your
network.
AT&T is America's best wireless
network,
according to America's biggest
test.
Now with 5G Evolution. The first
step to 5G.
MORE FOR YOUR THING. THAT'S OUR
THING.
>> Announcer: ONLINE NOW
READ THE STORY ABOUT THE HIGH
YIELDING STOCKS TAKING WALL
STREET BY STORM.
WE'RE TALKINGMORRIS,
WESTERN DIGITAL, EXXONMOBIL AND
MORE
GO TO CNBC.COM
>> WE'RE BACK ABOUT A MINUTE TO
GO
KATE MOORE THANKS FOR BEING
HERE
>> WE'RE GOING TO GO LARGE
CAPTION OVER SMALL CAPS ON THIS
ONE.
SMALL CAPS ARE GEARED TO
INTERNATIONAL CHAINS AND SUPPLY
CHAINS
THEY ARE TRADING KAT VALUATIONS
BUT ALMOST ALL THE RETURNS FROM
MULTIPLE EXPANSION THIS YEAR AND
WE ACTUALLY THINK YOU WANT TO BE
HIGHER IN QUALITY AS UNCERTAINTY
GETS GREATER AS WE GO TO THE
SECOND QUARTER
>> I ACTUALLY LIKE CHINA
I LIKE THE PLAY ON CHINA
I LIKE THE PROSPECTS ON CLINE.
GIVEN THE MSCI INCREASED THEIR
EXPOSURE, CHINA TO ASIA 5% TO
25%, THE EXPOSURE WILL B