BECAUSE, LIKE YOU SAY, BRANDING
FOR NIKE IS SECOND NATURE.
THEY HAVE ALMOST DEFINED THE
BRAND FOR US.
>> YEAH.
WE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT THAT SWOOSH
WAS.
>> WITH THE MARKETING, YEAH.
AND SIGNING KAEPERNICK, YOU
KNOW, IN THOSE MOMENTS IN WHICH
THERE WAS A LOT OF CRITICISM
WHICH WILL THEY KNEW THEY WERE
GOING TO GET, THE BURNING OF THE
SHOES AND THE REST OF IT.
IN THE IMMEDIATE MOMENTS AFTER
THAT, THEY DID ACTUALLY SEE THE
STOCK PRICES GO UP AND THE SHOE
SALES GO UP.
IT'S INTERESTING TO SEE WHAT
HAPPENS NOW AND THE REACTION TO
THIS CONTROVERSY WAS THE RIGHT
STEP. STEPHANIE GOSK, THANK YOU.
CONNECT WITH THE SHOW AT "VELSHI
& RUHLE."
KASIE HUNT PICKS UP THE COVERAGE
RIGHT NOW.
HELLO, FRIEND.
>> HELLO TO YOU, ALI.
I'M KASIE HUNT.
THE PRESIDENT'S OWN DEPARTMENT
OF HOMELAND SECURITY HAS ISSUED
A SCATHING REPORT ON THE SQUALID
CONDITIONS FOUND IN A NUMBER OF
MIGRANT DETENTION CENTERS ALONG
THE BORDER.
THE REPORT FROM THE DHS' OFFICE
OF THE INSPECTOR GENERAL
DESCRIBES DANGEROUS LEVELS OF
OVERCROWDING FOR LONG PERIODS OF
TIME.
IN ONE FACILITY, SOME ADULTS
WERE KEPT IN STANDING ROOM ONLY
CONDITIONS FOR A WEEK.
WHILE IN ANOTHER, MANY MIGRANTS
SPENT MORE THAN A MONTH IN SMALL
CELLS PACKED DANGEROUSLY OVER
CAPACITY.
MOST OF THE ADULTS HAVE NOT HAD
A SHOWER DESPITE SOME OF THEM
BEING HELD AS LONG AS A MONTH.
SOME FACILITIES PROVIDED WET
WIPES TO MAINTAIN HYGIENE.
ONE MAN BLOCKED IN A CROWDED
CELL HELD UP A CRUDELY MADE SIGN
FOR INSPECTORS BEGGING FOR HELP.
MEANWHILE, MANY CHILDREN WERE
HELD WITHOUT CARE FOR BASIC
STANDARDS OF LIVING INCLUDING
ACCESS TO SHOWERS AND CLEAN
CLOTHES.
AT TWO OF THE FIVE FACILITIES
VISITED BY THE INSPECTOR GENERAL
CHILDREN WERE NOT GIVE HOT MEALS
UNTILSPECTORS ARRIVED.
BUT ACCORDING TO THE PRESIDENT
AND HIS ALLIES THERE'S NOTHING
HERE.
KEVIN McALEENAN WHO DEFENDS THE
CONDITIONS AT ONE NOTORIOUS
CENTER LAST WEEK.
>> UNSUBSTANTIATED CONDITIONS
LAST WEEK AT A STATE FACILITY IN
TEXAS CREATED A SENSATION.
THAT'S BALANCD SOMEWHAT SINCE
SEVERAL MEDIA OUTLETS VISITED
AND SAW A CLEAN FACILITY.
MUCH OF THE COVERAGE IS TOO LATE
AND IS MISSING THE STORY.
>> SO, OUR BIG QUESTION TODAY IS
WILL THE WHITE HOUSE ACCEPT
ACCOUNTABILITY FOR ITS
IMMIGRATION POLICIES?
JOINING ME NOW NBC NEWS
CORRESPONDENT JACOB SOBOROFF.
FORMER CORRESPONDENT CARLOS
CARVALHO AND BARBARA BOXER WHO
HOSTS THE BOXER PODCAST.
JACOB, LET ME START WITH YOU.
THE REPORT FROM THE OIG.
I'M GOING TO READ FROM IT.
SENIOR MANAGERS AT SEVERAL
FACILITIES RAISED SECURITY
CONCERNS FOR THEIR AGENTS AND
DETAINEES.
FOR EXAMPLE, ONE CALLED THE
SITUATION A TICKING TIME BOMB.
IT REALLY UNDERSCORES THE FACT
THAT THEY SEEM TO HAVE
UNDERSTOOD JUST HOW BAD THINGS
HAD GOTTEN.
AND JUST HOW MUCH OF A PROBLEM
THIS WAS GOING TO BE.
AND YET, NOTHING SEEMS TO BE
DONE.
>> YEAH, YOU HIT THE NAIL ON THE
HEAD, KASIE.
AND I THINK THE TICKING TIME
BOMB VERY CLEARLY REFERENCES AND
IS AN ACCURATE DESCRIPTION OF
THE SEVEN FACILITIES IN THE RIO
GRANDE VALLEY.
BUT NOT ONLY THERE, IT CAN BE
APPLIED TO THE FACILITIES THAT
JULIA AINSLEY AND I REPORTED ON
EARLIER THIS WEEK IN THE EL PASO
SECTOR.
AND FRANKLY THAT PHRASE, A
TICKING TIME BOMB, CAN BE
ASCRIBED TO THE BORDER PATROL
SYSTEM THAT'S BEEN IN THIS
COUNTRY FOR DECADES.
IT'S NEVER BEEN WORSE THAN IT IS
RIGHT NOW IN THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION SEEING MORE
FAMILIES COMING HERE,
PARTICULARLY BECAUSE OF THE
METERING POLICIES THAT ARE
FORCING PEOPLE TO CROSS ILLEGAL
WITH, BECAUSE THEY DON'T WANT TO
WAIT IN ONE OF THE MOST
DANGEROUS COUNTRIES IN THE
WORLD, MEXICO.
BUT FOR YEARS, WE HAVE KNOWN
THOSE DETENTION FACILITIES ARE
DESIGNED FOR SINGLE ADULT MEN.
AND AS YOU HAVE PEOPLE THAT HAVE
COME TO CLAIM UNACCOMPANIED
MINORS.
WITH FAMILIES IN THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION, THOSE FACILITIES
ARE NOT SUITABLE FOR THE PEOPLE
THAT ARE WE'RE SEEING CROSS OUR
BORDER LARGELY ASYLUM SEEKERS.
SO YOU COULD CALL THEM A TICKING
TIME BOMB OVER THE COURSE OF THE
LAST YEAR.
FRANKLY, THEY'VE BEEN A TICKING
TIME BOMB FOR DECADES, KASIE.
>> JACOB, THE WHITE HOUSE MUST
HAVE HAD AN ADVANCED NOTICE OF
THIS REPORT, NO?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF THE WHITE
HOUSE HAD KNOWLEDGE OF WHAT WAS
GOING ON AT THESE FACILITIES AND
WHAT THE OFFICE OF INSPECTOR
GENERAL AND DEPARTMENT OF
HOMELAND SECURITY WAS FINDING
BUT THEY CERTAINLY HAD
CONVERSATIONS WITH MEMBERS OF
THE HOMELAND SECURITY THEY'VE
KNOWN AND I'M SURE THE PRESIDENT
IS GETTING REPORTS WHO IS
CROSSING THE BORDERS.
WHERE THESE FOLKS HAVE BEEN
DETAINED ULTIMATELY WHERE THEY
WANT TO GO AND WHY THEY COME TO
THIS COUNTRY.
IDEA THAT MAYBE THIS IS A
SURPRISE TO THE WHITE HOUSE, YOU
KNOW, DOESN'T SQUARE WITH THE
INFORMATION THAT'S AVAILABLE TO
THEM FROM THEIR OWN DEPARTMENT
OF HOMELAND SECURITY.
I KNOW THEY'RE PLUGGED IN DAILY
ON WHAT'S GOING ON AT THE
BORDER.
>> CONGRESSWOMAN CARVALHO, YOU
TRIED TO VISIT A DETENTION
FACILITY AND WERE DENIED ACCESS
WHEN YOU WERE A MEMBER OF
CONGRESS.
AND YOU ARE A REPUBLICAN, ALBEIT
ONE WHO HAS ADVOCATED AT TIMES
FOR AN IMMIGRATION POLICY THAT
IS DIFFERENT THAN WHAT THIS
ADMINISTRATION HAS, OBVIOUSLY,
PUSHED.
WHAT IS YOUR VIEW ON WHAT THE
ADMINISTRATION NEEDS TO BE DOING
RIGHT NOW TO HELP THE PEOPLE WHO
ARE IN THESE DETENTION CENTERS?
>> WELL, KASIE, LET ME SAY THIS
WOULD BE A DIFFICULT SITUATION
FOR ANY ADMINISTRATION.
3, 4, 5,000 PEOPLE ARE COMING
ACROSS THE BORDER.
THIS IS A NEW KIND OF
IMMIGRATION.
NOT LIKE WE USED TO SEE 10, 15
YEARS AGO.
THIS IS A DIFFICULT CHALLENGE, I
THINK WE HAVE TO BE FAIR AND REC
THIS THAT.
THE OTHER THING IS THERE'S A
MAJOR DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THE
DETENTION FACILITIES NEAR THE
BORDER AND THOSE IN OTHER PARTS
OF THE COUNTRY.
DOWN HERE IN SOUTH FLORIDA,
THERE ARE A FEW OF THEM
DEDICATED TO MINORS AND THE
CONDITIONS ARE A LOT BETTER THAN
THE IMAGES WE'VE SEEN COMING
FROM THE BORDER.
BUT THE FACT REMAINS, THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS TO DO BETTER.
AND THAT THEY WOULD JUST BRUSH
OFF THIS REPORT FROM THE
DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND SECURITY
IS UNACCEPTABLE.
CONGRESS HAS TO DO MORE TO
DEDICATE MORE FUNDING TO UPDATE
THESE FACILITIES TO MAKE SURE
THEY'RE COMPATIBLE, THE KIND OF
IMMIGRATION WE'RE SEEING COMING
INTO OUR COUNTRY.
AND, OF COURSE, THE LAWS DO HAVE
TO BE CHANGED BECAUSE
UNFORTUNATELY, THE WAY OUR LAWS
ARE DESIGNED, THEY DO INVITE
PEOPLE TO COME OVER WITH
CHILDREN SPECIFICALLY BECAUSE
THE COYOTES ADVERTISE THAT AS A
MORE ADVANTAGEOUS STRATEGY FOR
TRYING TO COME TO THE UNITED
STATES.
SO, THIS IS A COMPLEX,
COMPLICATED PROBLEM.
AND UNFORTUNATELY, I DON'T THINK
THIS WHITE HOUSE IS TAKING IT AS
SERIOUSLY AS THEY SHOULD.
>> SENATOR BOXER, THERE IS,
THOUGH, I TAKE THE CONGRESSMAN'S
POINT.
BUT THERE'S STILL A LOT OF
DECISIONS THAT ANY DECISION THAT
THE ADMINISTRATION MAY MAKE ON
HOW PEOPLE ARE CROSSING OUR
BORDERS.
WHAT COULD THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION BE DOING
DIFFERENTLY TODAY TO TRY AND
MAKE THIS BETTER?
>> LISTEN, I'M GOING TO TALK IN
VERY STARK TERMS HERE.
WHAT WE SEE IS NOT A TICKING
TIME BOMB.
THE BOMB HAS GONE OFF FOR SEVEN
CHILDREN WHO DIED.
FOR THESE LITTLE BABIES THAT
HAVE BLUE FINGERS BECAUSE
THEY'RE FREEZING.
THESE PARENTS WHO WERE TOLD
REPORTEDLY, DRINK OUT OF THE
TOILET BECAUSE THERE'S NO FRESH
WATER.
THIS IS NATURE YOU HAVE TO DO
BETTER TIME.
THIS IS WE'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE
THIS DONE IN OUR NAME TIME.
AND WE HAVE TO FIX IT.
IT'S A STAIN ON AMERICA.
IT'S BEING DONE IN OUR NAME.
SO, WHAT DO WE DO?
THE FIRST THING IS, WE BRING
BACK THE MODEL PROJECT THAT
BARACK OBAMA HAD IN PLACE THAT
WORKED VERY WELL AS AN
ALTERNATIVE TO DETENTION WHERE
98% OF THE PEOPLE SHOWED UP FOR
THEIR COURT DATE.
AND SECONDLY, WE NEED A SURGE OF
CASEWORKERS.
BETO O'ROURKE HAS SUGGESTED
THIS.
CASEWORKERS FOR THESE VARIOUS
CASES SO THEY CAN BE FOLLOWED.
SO THEY FOLLOW THE RULES, AND
THEY'RE TAKEN CARE OF.
AND WE KNOW THAT THIS -- YOU
KNOW, DETERRENCE IS A STRATEGY
OF TRUMP.
AND HOW DOES HE THINK HE'S GOING
TO DETER PEOPLE?
BY MAKING THEM GO THROUGH AGONY.
THIS IS NOT AMERICA.
IT NEEDS TO STOP, PERIOD.
>> JACOB SOBOROFF.
>> RESPECTIVELY, TO BOTH THE
SENATOR AND THE CONGRESSMAN,
BOTH OF YOU SERVED WHEN THESE
FACILITIES WERE ALREADY IN
PLACE.
IN 2014, PRESIDENT OBAMA HAD A
SURGE OF UNACCOMPANIED MIGRANT
CHILDREN IN FACILITIES JUST LIKE
THIS AND WE SAW PICTURES JUST
LIKE THIS.
SO, THESE CONDITIONS ARE NOT
NEW.
I DO AGREE WITH, SENATOR BOXER,
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS MADE THIS
WORSE THAN EVER BEFORE.
CONGRESSMAN CURBELO, I HAVE BEEN
TO THAT HOMESTEAD FACILITY IN
SOUTH FLORIDA, I WAS JUST THERE
LAST WEEK.
WHERE ARE CHILDREN ARE CURRENTLY
LIVING IN THE CUSTODY OF HHS.
CERTAINLY, THE FACILITY IS THERE
BETTER AND THE LICENSED DAY CARE
WORKERS TO TAKE CARE OF
CHILDREN.
BUT WE DIDN'T HAVE ANY WARNING
TO THIS, THAT THE TICKING TIME
BOMB IS JUST LIMITED TO THIS
TIME PERIOD NOW, I DON'T THINK
IS FAIR.
I THINK THE IMMIGRATION
DETENTION SYSTEM HAS BEEN PLACED
ON DETERRENCE IN THE CLINTON
ADMINISTRATION.
THERE WAS A DOCUMENT PUT OUT
PREFERENCE THROUGH DETEARENCE.
THEY'VE KNOWN FROM THE BUSH
ADMINISTRATION INTO THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION AND NOW WITH THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION WORSE THAN
EVER BEFORE WAS ALWAYS FORCING
PEOPLE TO TAKE MORE DANGER
OPTION AND DEADLY ROUTES INTO
THIS COUNTRY.
AND THE CONDITIONS THEY WERE
HOUSED IN, ONCE IN DETENTION,
WERE NEVER MEANT FOR PEOPLE TO
STAY OVER 72 HOURS.
WE HAVE SEEN STUFF LIKE THIS
BEFORE.
IT'S JUST NOT AS BAD AS IT IS
TODAY.
>> SENATOR --
>> CAN I MENTION --
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> THE REALITY HERE IS THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION VIEW ON
IMMIGRATION HAS BEEN CRITICIZED.
YOUR RESPONSE.
>> IT'S ALL FINE.
IT'S ALL FINE.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS, WE CAN LOOK
BACK TO THOSE DAYS WHERE THERE
WERE THESE ISSUES BUT I WOULD
ARGUE THERE'S NOTHING, NOTHING
TO THIS EXTENT.
THIS IS DETERRENCE BY AGONY.
THAT'S WHAT WE HAVE.
IT'S JUST UNREAL.
AND I VOTED FOR COMPREHENSIVE
IMMIGRATION REFORM.
HAD PAUL RYAN ALLOWED THAT TO GO
TO VOTE WE WOULDN'T HAVE ANY OF
THIS NOW.
WE CAN ARGUE ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
IN 2014.
I'M UP FOR THAT, I'M NOT
ABSOLVING ANYBODY.
WHAT I'M SAYING IS, THIS IS
HAPPENING NOW.
LET'S FIX IT NOW.
>> RIGHT.
>> LET'S SURGE THE JUDGES, LET'S
SURGE THE CASEWORKERS.
LET'S GO BACK TO OBAMA'S PLAN
WHICH WAS AN ALTERNATIVE TO
DETENTION THAT JAKE CAN'T
MENTION THAT WAS WORKING REALLY
WELL.
LET'S TRY IT.
I DON'T CARE -- I'M NOT SAYING
EVERYONE HAS BEEN WONDERFUL ON
THIS.
I'M NOT SAYING I'VE BEEN
WONDERFUL ON THIS.
IT'S HAPPENING NOW.
AND I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING, I
WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED IF THERE'S
SOME KIND OF COMPLAINT TO THE
WORLD COURT ABOUT THIS, THAT
THERE ARE CRIMES AGAINST
HUMANITY GOING ON IN OUR NAME.
IN OUR NAME.
>> CONGRESSMAN, JUMP IN.
>> LET ME JUST SAY BRIEFLY, THE
ADMINISTRATION DESERVES A LOT OF
THE CRITICISM IT RECEIVES.
AND CERTAINLY ON IMMIGRATION.
I WAS AN OUTSPOKEN CRITIC WHILE
I WAS IN CONGRESS ON THIS
ADMINISTRATION.
I WILL SAY WEE NEED A LITTLE
SOBRIETY HERE.
WE NEED TO TAKE NOTE OF THE FACT
THIS IS AN EXTRAORDINARY SET OF
CIRCUMSTANCES.
I REMEMBER IN 1994, WHEN OVER
13,000 CUBANS ATTEMPTED TO COME
ACROSS THE FLORIDA STRAIT.
THEY SET UP TENT COMPANIES AT
GUANTANAMO BAY AT GITMO.
IT'S EXTRAORDINARY.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN IT'S
EXTRAORDINARY FOR THE CONDITIONS
THAT HAVE BEEN REPORTED OUT OF
THESE FACILITIES TO BE PRESENT,
THAT WILL HAVE TO CHANGE.
BUT AGAIN, THIS IS NOT A REGULAR
TIME WHEN IT COMES TO ILLEGAL
IMMIGRATION INTO OUR COUNTRY,
AND WE JUST SIMPLY HAVE TO TAKE
THAT INTO ACCOUNT IN EVALUATING
WHAT'S HAPPENING AT THE BORDER.
>> BUT DON'T YOU THINK,
CONGRESSMAN -- I DO TAKE YOUR
POINT THAT THIS IS AN
EXTRAORDINARY CIRCUMSTANCE.
BUT THESE PEOPLE ARE SUFFERING,
AS THE SENATOR SAID --
>> AND THAT'S TOTALLY
UNACCEPTABLE.
AND WHAT WE NEED IS FOR CONGRESS
TO FUND NEW FACILITIES THAT ARE
COMPATIBLE TO THE TYPE OF
IMMIGRATION WE'RE GETTING INTO
OUR COUNTRY.
IT'S NOT MEN CROSSING THE BORDER
LOOKING FOR WORK ANYMORE.
IT'S FAMILIES, IT'S CHILDREN.
AND THESE FACILITIES AREN'T
DESIGNED TO HOLD THEM.
AND WE NEED FACILITIES THAT CAN
HOLD THESE FAMILIES WHILE THEIR
CASES ARE BEING ADJUDICATED AND
PROCESSED.
>> CAN I QUICKLY JUMP IN?
>> VERY QUICKLY, JACOB.
WE'VE GOT TO GO TO BREAK.
>> WHAT THE CONGRESSMAN IS
SUGGESTING HERE AND CORRECT ME
IF I'M WRONG, WHAT THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION IS SUGGESTING AND
WHAT THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
ALSO WANTED TO DO WAS TO TURN
AROUND UNDOCUMENTED MIGRANT
CHILDREN FROM CENTRAL AMERICA.
DEPORT THEM IMMEDIATELY AND/OR
DETAIN FAMILIES INDEFINITELY.
INSTEAD OF RELEASING THEM INTO
THE INTERIOR.
WHEN YOU SAY WE NEED TO CHANGE
THE LAWS, I THINK WE NEED TO GO
DEEPER ON WHAT CHANGING THE LAWS
ACTUALLY MEANS.
>> WELL, JACOB, REAL QUICK, IT
DOESN'T HAVE TO BE THAT WAY.
WE CAN PRIORITIZE CASE WHERE IS
MINORS ARE INVOLVED SO THEY CAN
BE PROCESSED IMMEDIATELY, NOT
THAT THEY'RE HELD MONTHS AND
MONTHS, BUT MAYBE TWO OR THREE
WEEKS UNTIL THOSE CASES ARE
ADJUDICATED.
>> CAN I JUST SAY --
>> I'M SORRY, SENATOR.
WE HAVE TO GO.
>> IT IS.
IT IS.
>> THIS IS AN EMOTIONAL DEBATE.
AND THAT IS A POLICY THAT WE'VE
DISCUSSED ON THE PROGRAM.
THANK YOU ALL VERY MUCH.
>>> STILL TO COME THIS HOUR, NEW
CONCERNS JUST HOURS BEFORE THE
FOURTH OF JULY CELEBRATION IN
WASHINGTON, INCLUDING REPORTS
THAT ONLY TRUMP SUPPORTERS WILL
GET A FRONT ROW SEAT TO THE
PRESIDENT'S SALUTE TO AMERICA.
>>> PLUS, IOWA, IOWA, IOWA.
KAMALA HARRIS HEADS TO THE FIRST
CAUCUS STATE USING THEY ARE
POST-DEBATE SURGE IN POLLING TO
CLOSE IN ON JOE BIDEN.
>>> RIGHT AFTER THIS BREAK, WHY
THE PRESIDENT'S CAMPAIGN IS
REPORTEDLY CONCERNED THAT THEY
MAY NOT HAVE A MAJOR TOOL IN ITS
POLITICAL ARSENAL COME 2020.
0.
>>> THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IS
REPORTEDLY SWEATING BULLETS OVER
WHAT SOME ARE DESCRIBING AS A
MELTDOWN AT THE NATIONAL RIFLE
ASSOCIATION.
POLITICO REPORTING TODAY, QUOTE,
THE TURMOIL IS FUELLING FEARS
THAT THE ORGANIZATION WILL BE
PROFOUNDLY DIMINISHED HEADING
INTO THE ELECTION, LEAVING THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY WITH A GAPING
HOLE IN ITS POLITICAL MACHINERY.
THE PRESIDENT CALLED THE NRA A,
QUOTE, VICTIM OF HARASSMENT IN A
TWEET THIS WEEK SAYING THAT THE
GUN RIGHTS GROUP THAT HELPS GET
INTO THE WHITE HOUSE MIGHT MOVE
TO TEXAS WHERE THEY ARE LOVED.
HE SUGGESTED THE NRA CAN GET
BETTER PROTECTION THERE FROM THE
NEW YORK STATE INVESTIGATION
INTO THE GROUP'S TAX EXEMPT
STATUS.
BUT THE ATTENTION FROM THE
PRESIDENT COMES AMID MULTIPLE
OTHER REPORTS AROUND THE
FRACTURE AT THE NRA, INCLUDING
AN UGLY DISPUTE OVER LEADERSHIP
OF THE ORGANIZATION.
JOINING ME THE POLITICO REPORTER
AND MSNBC CONTRIBUTOR BETSY
WOODRUFF.
THANK YOU BOTH.
ALEX, THIS WAS YOUR STORY IN
POLITICO, JUST HOW CONCERNED THE
PRESIDENT'S CAMPAIGN WAS ABOUT,
FRANKLY, SEEMS LIKE A TOTAL
COLLAPSE AT THE NRA.
OR THE INABILITY TO LOOK
OUTWARD.
WHAT DOES IT MEAN POTENTIALLY
FOR THE PRESIDENT'S RE-ELECT?
>> IT'S HARD TO POINT OUT HOW
IMPORTANT IT IS FOR THE NRA FOR
THE TURNOUT APPARATUS TO THE
ELECTIONS.
THE NRA HAS OVER 5 MILLION
MEMBERS AND THE DUES PAYING
MEMBERS THAT YOU HAVE, FOR THEM,
THE NRA IS A VERY IMPORTANT --
IT'S A VERY IMPORTANT
ORGANIZATION.
SO THEY CAN REALLY TURN OUT
VOTERS.
AND THEY CAN TURN OUT VOTERS FOR
THE REPUBLICAN SIDE.
WITHOUT THEM ON THE FIELD THAT
CAN HAVE BIG IMPLICATIONS FOR
THE GOP COME 2020.
>> BETSY, YOU'VE DONE A LOT OF
REPORTING ON KIND OF HOW THE
BOTTOM HAS FALLEN OUT ON THE NRA
AND HOW THEY HAVE TURNED ON EACH
OTHER.
WHAT IS YOUR ASSESSMENT ROOTED
IN THAT ON HOW EFFECTIVE IT IS
IN 2020?
>> THE BIGGEST QUESTION IS
MONEY.
IS THE NRA ABLE TO REPLICATE THE
MASSIVE EXPENDITURES IT MADE ON
TRUMP'S RAISE IN 2012016?
THERE WERE SOME VOICES ACCORDING
TO MY VOICES WHO SAID THIS TRUMP
GUY DOESN'T LOOK LIKE THESE
GOING VERY FAR.
MAYBE WE SHOULD FOCUS ON
CONGRESS MAKING SURE THAT THE
POTENTIAL PRESIDENT CLINTON
WOULD HAVE MAJORITY IN THE HOUSE
AND SENATE.
BUT SEVERAL LEADERSHIP FIGURES
IN THE NRA INCLUDING PEOPLE I'VE
SPOKEN TO CHRIS COX ARGUED, NO,
WE NEED TO GO ALL IN, AND WE
NEED TO SPEND BIG ON TRUMP.
CHRIS COX WHO USED TO BE THE TOP
LOBBYIST AT THE NRA JUST
OFFICIALLY LEFT THE ASSOCIATION
WITHIN THE LAST FEW DAYS.
HOW THAT LEADERSHIP VOID IS
GOING TO BE FILLED IS REALLY
IMPORTANT.
AND, OF COURSE, THE HUGE
QUESTION IS ARE THE NRA'S
FINANCIAL PROBLEMS GOING TO
LIMIT HOW BIG OF A WAR CHEST
THEY HAD TO SPEND ON TRUMP.
OLIVER NORTH WHO WAS FORMALLY
THE PRESIDENT OF NRA DEPOSED AND
DESCRIBED AS A COUP, WROTE THAT
THE NRA UPWARDS OF $120 MILLION
UPWARDS JUST FOR LEGAL EXPENSES.
IF THEY'RE SPENDING ON LEGAL
BILLS AT THAT SCALE THAT'S A LOT
OF MONEY FOR A NONPROFIT.
AND IT'S MONEY THEY CAN'T SPEND
IN 2020.
>> BETSY, HOW MUCH OF THIS HAS
TRICKLED DOWN TO WHAT ALEX WAS
SAYING THAT PEOPLE SHOW UP AND
DO WHAT THE NRA ASKED THEM TO
DO?
ARE THEY STARTING TO GET
NERVOUS?
>> LOOK.
IT'S HARD TO SEE HOW FAR IT'S
TRICKLED OUT.
AND THERE'S A LOT OF SKEPTICISM
WITH THE MAINSTREAM MEDIA.
THEY VIEW THE REPORTERS WHO
COVER THESE ISSUES AS GENERALLY
HOSTILE TO WHAT THEY CARE ABOUT.
AS FAR AS AN AUDIENCE, IT'S MORE
SKEPTICAL.
AT THE SAME TIME, OF COURSE,
IT'S FRUSTRATING BOARD MEMBERS.
ALAN WEST WHO IS A CONSERVATIVE
FAN FAVORITE IS A MEMBER OF NRA
BOARD AND HAS CALLED FOR WANE
LAPIERRE TO BE DEPOSED.
AND IF YOU LOOK AT THE COMMENTS
ON THE YOUTUBE GUN PAGES YOU'LL
SEE A TON OF FRICTION AND TON OF
CRITICISM PARTICULARLY OF NRA
CEO WAYNE LAPIERRE.
>> ALEX, YOU WRITE THAT THIS
GOES BEYOND REPUBLICANS.
CALLING ON THE NRA TO ADDRESS
IT.
AND EXPRESSING VIEWS TO TODD
YOUNG.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
REPUBLICANS ARE TRYING TO
PROTECT THEIR SENATE MAJORITY IN
2020.
A LOT OF SENATORS ELECTED IN
2016 WON WITH THE HELP OF THE
NATIONAL RIFLE ASSOCIATION.
YOU CAN BET IT'S NOT JUST THE
TRUMP CAMPAIGN COUNTING ON THE
NRA TO TURN OUT VOTERS IN
CRITICAL STATES LIKE MICHIGAN,
PENNSYLVANIA, WISCONSIN, THOSE
IMPORTANT RUST BELT STATES.
IT'S ALSO GOING TO BE SENATORS
UP FOR RE-ELECTION IN 2020.
YOU'RE LIKELY TO HEAR A LOT MORE
FROM THEM IN THE WEEKS TO COME.
>> A LOT AT STAKE.
THANK YOU BOTH VERY MUCH.
GREAT TO SEE YOU.
>>> WITH HER POLLING ON THE
RISE, CAN KAMALA HARRIS CREATE A
WINNING COALITION LIKE FORMER
PRESIDENT OBAMA'S?
If you have moderate to
severe psoriasis
or psoriatic arthritis,
little things
can be a big deal.
That's why there's Otezla.
Otezla is not an injection
or a cream.
It's a pill that treats
differently.
For psoriasis, 75% clearer
skin is achievable,
with reduced redness, thickness,
and scaliness of plaques.
For psoriatic arthritis, Otezla
is proven to reduce joint
swelling, tenderness, and pain.
And the Otezla Prescribing
information has no requirement
for routine lab monitoring.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Otezla.
It may cause severe diarrhea,
nausea, or vomiting.
Otezla is associated with an
increased risk of depression.
Tell your doctor if you have a
history of depression
or suicidal thoughts
or if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor your
weight and may stop treatment.
Upper respiratory tract
infection
and headache may occur.
Tell your doctor about
your medicines
and if you're pregnant
or planning to be.
Ready to treat differently
with a pill?
Otezla. Show more of you.
>>> AFTER A STANDOUT DEBATE
PERFORMANCE SENATOR KAMALA
HARRIS WILL CAMPAIGN IN IOWA
TODAY.
IT'S A PLACE WHERE SUPPORT FOR
THE CALIFORNIA CANDIDATE APPEARS
TO BE SURGING, ACCORDING TO
SEVERAL POST-DEBATE POLLS.
A NEW "USA TODAY" SUFFOLK
UNIVERSITY POLL PUTS HARRIS IN
SECOND PLACE WITH 17th PERCENT
IN THE EARLY CAUCUS STATE.
THE SENATOR'S RISE HAS SOME
PEOPLE WONDER WHETHER SHE CAN
FOLLOW IN OBAMA'S FOOT STEPS.
QUOTE, THE QUESTION TURNS ON THE
NOTION OF ELECTABILITY.
AN OBSESSION FOR PRIMARY VOTERS
ON ITS HEAD THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN
UNCONCEIVABLE JUST A WEEK AGO.
LIKE OBAMA, HARRIS HAILS FROM
HER PARTY'S ESTABLISHMENT BUT IT
IS A RELATIVELY FRESH FACE WITH
ONLY TWO YEARS IN HER SENATE.
SHE HAS POSITIONS WHICH CAN MAKE
THEY ARE APPEALING TO MORE
LIBERAL YOUNG VOTERS.
VAUGHN HILLYARD, ALEX SETWALD.
AND OUR WASHINGTON CORRESPONDENT
AND MSNBC CONTRIBUTOR.
OBVIOUSLY, THE POLLS HAVE BEEN
GOOD FOR SENATOR HARRIS.
BUT I'M CURIOUS WHAT YOU'RE
PICKING UP BEHIND THE SCENES
WITH THE CAMPAIGN.
I MEAN, CLEARLY MANY OF HER
STAFFERS HAVE BEEN PRETTY GIDDY
ABOUT HER PERFORMANCE.
AND IT IS STARTING TO SHOW UP IN
THE NUMBERS.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, THEY'VE
MADE A RISKY STRATEGY BET HERE.
AND THERE ARE ALSO QUESTIONS IF
SHE IS GOING TO GO IN IOWA, THIS
POLL WOULD SUGGEST PERHAPS SHE
CAN.
WHAT ARE YOU PICKING UP ON?
>> EXACTLY.
THIS IS A CAMPAIGN THAT LOOKED
AT THEIR POLLING SITTING AT 6%,
7%, 8%, EVER SINCE HER LAUNCH
BACK IN JANUARY.
AND THE CAMPAIGN ALWAYS LOOKED
AT THIS AS THE DEBATE BEING AN
OPPORTUNITY TO INTRODUCE
HERSELF.
AS ALEX POINTED OUT IN HIS PIECE
THERE, SHE'S JUST IN HER THIRD
YEAR IN THE UNITED STATES SENATE
OUT OF CALIFORNIA.
THE DEBATE WAS AN OPPORTUNITY TO
SPEAK IN FRONT OF 20 MILLION
PEOPLE AND ESSENTIALLY INTRODUCE
HERSELF.
AND WHAT THE CAMPAIGN HAS BEEN
COMPELLED TO MAKE THE CASE ON
FROM GOING THROUGH THE LIKES OF
MICHIGAN DOWN INTO LOUISIANA
THROUGH THIS PRIMARY PROCESS, IS
THAT KAMALA HARRIS IS A GENERAL
ELECTION CANDIDATE.
BARACK OBAMA FOR ONE SHOULD KNOW
WON THE IOWA CAUCUS OVER THE
LIKES OF JOHN EDWARDS AND
HILLARY CLINTON.
HE ALSO WON THE STATE OF IOWA
NOT ONLY OVER JOHN McCAIN, BUT
JOHN KERRY.
IN PLACES LIKE IN IOWA, ALSO IN
MICHIGAN AND DRIVE HIGHER
TURNOUT IN PLACES LIKE THE
DETROIT AREA, OR AROUND THE
PARTS OF MILWAUKEE, ESSENTIALLY,
WHEN YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
ELECTABILITY, KAMALA HARRIS IS
YOUR CANDIDATE.
THAT'S THE CASE SHE'S TRYING TO
MAKE OVER THE NEXT TWO DAYS IN
IOWA TO IOWANS.
>> ANEESH, WHAT HAVE YOU SEEN ON
THIS QUESTION OF IOWA.
YOU KNOW, IT'S TRUE THAT BARACK
OBAMA WAS, YOU KNOW, AN
AFRICAN-AMERICAN WHO APPEALED TO
A LARGELY WHITE ELECTORATE IN
IOWA AND SET HIM ON THE PATH TO
THE PRESIDENCY.
AND THE COALITION WE'RE SEEING
BEHIND THIS POLLING IS WHITE
LIBERALS AND INCREASINGLY
AFRICAN-AMERICANS.
IS THIS A TRAJECTORY THAT CAN
HOLD?
>> IT'S A TRAJECTORY THAT CAN
HOLD IF SHE CAN WEATHER THE
STORM OF AN INTENSE BACKGROUND
WITH HER STANCE ON ALL SORTS OF
THINGS AS A PROSECUTOR.
I'VE TALKED TO SOME DEMOCRATIC
CONSULTANTS WHO SAY THERE'S
GOING TO BE A NUMBER OF
FRONT-RUNNERS GOING FORWARD.
RIGHT NOW, JOE BIDEN WAS SEEN AS
THE PERSON LEADING THE PACK.
KAMALA HARRIS I SHOULD ALSO SAY
ARE ON THE RISE.
I THINK WHAT WE'RE GOING TO LOOK
AT, WHETHER OR NOT AFTER PEOPLE
LEARN MORE ABOUT SENATOR HARRIS'
BACKGROUND INCLUDING ALL OF HER
CRIMINAL JUSTICE ISSUES AND HER
STANCES ON IMMIGRATION AND
HEALTH CARE.
WHERE SHE DIFFERS IN SOME WAYS
FROM OTHER CANDIDATES.
THINKING ABOUT SHE WOULD NOT
ELIMINATE PRIVATE INSURANCE FOR
GOVERNMENT-RUN INSURANCE.
I THINK ONCE PEOPLE START
DIGGING INTO HER, WE'LL HAVE TO
SEE WHETHER OR NOT SHE CAN HOLD
THAT COALITION TOGETHER BUT, OF
COURSE, PEOPLE ARE VERY EXCITED
ABOUT HER.
I THINK HER DEBATE PERFORMANCE
MADE A LOST OF PEOPLE SHE COULD
GO AFTER DONALD TRUMP.
SHE COULD BE ON STAGE WITH HIM,
LOOK HIM IN THE EYE AND GO TOE
TO TOE WITH HIM.
>> ALEX, ONE CRITICAL PIECE,
OBVIOUSLY, AFRICAN-AMERICAN
VOTERS.
THAT HAS BEEN THE MOST
IMPORTANT, I WOULD SAY, PIECE TO
JOE BIDEN'S SUPPORT.
YOU WRITE SUPPORT FOR BIDEN
AMONG BLACKS, A DEMOCRATIC
VOTING BLOC -- EXCUSE ME, THIS
IS A REUTERS POLL, NOT YOUR
YOURS.
MY APOLOGIES.
THEY BACKED TWO OUT OF TEN
COMPARED TO 4 OUT OF TEN IN THE
JUNE POLL FOR BIDEN.
THAT SEEMS TO BE MAKING INROADS,
WHAT'S GOING TO CEMENT THIS, IF
ANYTHING?
>> IT'S GOING TO UNITE HOPEFULLY
LIBERALS ON ONE HAND, GIVEN HER
BACKGROUND.
THE TWO GROUPS GOING, THE
LIBERALS AND THE
AFRICAN-AMERICANS THAT'S A
PRETTY UNSTOPPABLE COALITION.
THERE'S BEEN FOUR OR FIVE POLLS
AFTER THE DEBATE INCLUING
REUTERS, QUINNIPIAC YESTERDAY
THAT SHOWS HER CLIMBING AMONG
AMERICANS AND BIDEN.
IT HAS BEEN HER BIGGEST SOURCE
OF STRENGTH.
IT WAS HILLARY CLINTON'S IN
2016.
I THINK THE FIELD IS TOO BIG TO
CONSOLIDATE.
AFRICAN-AMERICANS, OBVIOUSLY,
CORY BOOKER IS STILL IN THE
RACE.
IF SHE CAN SOLIDIFY A BIG CHUNK
OF THEM, THAT WILL SOLIDIFY THE
BASE IN THE LONG RUN.
SHE'S A WOMAN AND WOMEN DID VERY
WELL IN 2018.
DEMOCRATS ARE VERY EXCITED ABOUT
VOTING FOR A WOMAN RIGHT NOW.
THE QUESTION IS SHE TOO LITTLE
FOR EVERYONE AND FALLEN TO THE
MIDDLE WHERE SHE HAS BEEN AHEAD
IN THE DEBATE.
OR CAN SHE NOW USE THE STRENGTH
OF THE DEBATE STAGE TO MOVE
FORWARD?
>> LET ME TAKE THAT LAST VOTE
WITH WOMEN VOTERS AHEAD.
LISA WARE AT THE "THE NEW YORK
TIMES" WROTE TODAY THINKING THAT
A WOMAN IS NOT THE RIGHT NOMINEE
IN 2016 -- OR IN 2020, BECAUSE A
WOMAN LOST TO DONALD TRUMP IN
2016.
AND THERE WAS A SOUTH CAROLINA
VOTER QUOTED IN HER STORY WHO
SUPPORTS HARRIS.
BUT THIS WOMAN WHO SAYS SHE IS
AN AFRICAN-AMERICAN WOMAN SAYS,
QUOTE, I DON'T THINK SHE CAN
WIN.
I'M SORRY TO HAVE TO SAY THAT,
SHE IS A WOMAN AND SHE IS BLACK.
AS A BLACK WOMAN MYSELF AS MUCH
AS WE WOULD LIKE TO BELIEVE THIS
IS THIS HUGE SHIFT IN THIS
COUNTRY, WE HAVE SEEN THE PEOPLE
HAVE TO FIGHT BACK.
HOW MUCH THIS RADAR CONTRIBUTED
TO HARRIS' STRUGGLE TO RISE.
SHE'S BROKEN OUT SINCE BUT SHE
WAS FLOATING BACK THERE FOR A
WHILE.
IS THIS WHY?
>> THIS IS A HUGE PROBLEM.
ELECTABILITY IS THE NUMBER ONE
THING DEMOCRATS SAY THEY CARE
ABOUT.
THE VERY FIRST VOTER JANUARY 6th
SAID I LOVE ELIZABETH WARREN BUT
I DON'T THINK THE COUNTRY IS
READY FOR A WOMAN.
IT WAS A MIDDLE AGED WOMAN WHO
TOLD ME THIS.
THE DATA, ON THE OTHER HAND SHOW
ME THIS IS NOT TRUE THAT WOMEN
ON THE BALLOT WIN JUST AS MUCH
AS MEN DO.
AND THE AUTHORIZATION OF WOMEN
IN POLITICS IS MORE FOR
CANDIDATES GETTING ON THE
BALLOTS, MORE THAN VOTERS
DISCRIMINATING AGAINST THEM WHEN
THEY'RE VOTING.
SO I THINK THE ELECTORATE IS
STARTING TO REALIZE THAT AND
COMBAT THE PERCEPTION --
>> I ALSO THINK BARACK OBAMA --
>> THE DIFFERENCE, OF COURSE,
BETWEEN WHAT -- THE DATA THAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT AND, YOU
KNOW, WHAT ACTUALLY IS PLAYING
OUT ON THE GROUND IS SOMETHING
THAT WE'VE NEVER HAD IT TESTED
AT THE PRESIDENTIAL LEVEL.
>> TRUE.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> I'LL ALSO SAY WHEN BARACK
OBAMA WAS RUNNING, THERE WERE SO
MANY AFRICAN-AMERICANS THAT TOLD
ME PERSONALLY I'M NOT SURE THIS
COUNTRY IS READY FOR IT.
THEN WHEN HE WON IN IOWA AND THE
DEBATES AND PEOPLE LISTENED TO
HIS MESSAGE AND BECAME INSPIRED
BY HIS CAMPAIGN.
PEOPLE SAID WE'RE GOING BEHIND
THIS AFRICAN-AMERICAN MAN.
THE SAME THING WITH IS THAT
RIGHT HARRIS.
I THINK HER DEBATE PERFORMANCE,
MAKING PEOPLE UNDERSTAND THAT
COULD BE AN AFRICAN-AMERICAN
WOMEN.
AND WHEN WE SAW PROGRESS IT WAS
AN AFRICAN-AMERICAN MAN PUSHING
THE BOUNDARIES.
IT WILL BE ELIZABETH WARREN OR
TULSI GABBARD, OR OTHER WOMEN TO
INSPIRE A NATION, IF THEY'RE TO
BE SUCCESSFUL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU GUYS, ALL, VERY MUCH.
>>> SO WITH BIDEN IN THE LEAD
AND HARRIS SURGING IN THESE
POLLS, WHAT ABOUT THE REST OF
THE FIELD?
WE'RE GOING TO CHECK IN WITH
NBC'S ROAD WARRIORS WHO ARE WITH
SENATORS WARREN AND SANDERS.
yo.
And here to listen
and help you through it all
is Bank of America.
With the expertise and know-how
you need
to reach that blissful state
of Done-ness.
So let's get after it.
♪ Everything is all right ♪
What would you like
the power to do?®
♪ All right ♪
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
the power to do?®
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 65 AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
>>> VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN IS
STILL ATOP EVERY POLL OUT THERE.
AND YES, CAVEAT, IT IS EARLY.
BUT ACCORDING TO THREE MAJOR
POLLS OUT SINCE THE DEBATES, A
FIELD OF FOUR, BIDEN, HARRIS,
WARREN AND SANDERS SEEM TO BE
SEPARATING FROM THE PACT.
AND QUINNIPIAC ASKED
SPECIFICALLY WHICH CAME OUT AS
FAVORITES, SENATOR SANDERS
ELIZABETH WARREN.
SHAQ, LET ME START WITH YOU,
SANDERS' SUPPORT HAS BEEN
SLIPPING IN THESE RECENT
NATIONAL POLLS.
YOU KNOW, I'VE SEEN SOME FLASHES
OF FRUSTRATION FROM SANDERS IN
THAT, HE FEELS AND WILL TELL
ANYONE -- HAD TOLD ME IN A
RECENT INTERVIEW, YOU KNOW, HE'S
THE REASON WHY WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT SOME OF THOSE POLICY
ISSUES, MEDICARE FOR ALL, ET
CETERA.
HOW IS THE CAMPAIGN, YOU KNOW,
TRYING TO GET THEIR FOOTING BACK
UNDERNEATH THEM?
>> YOU HIT THAT POINT, KASIE.
THERE ARE SO MANY MORE OPTIONS
FOR VOTERS IN THIS ELECTION WITH
SO MANY CANDIDATES THERE.
THAT'S WHY YOU HAVE SENATOR
SANDERS FOCUSED ON CONTACTING AS
MANY VOTERS AS HE CAN.
HE'S IN THE MIDDLE OF A
THREE-DAY SWING THROUGH THE
STATE OF IOWA AND WHAT'S
INTERESTING WHAT HE'S
HIGHLIGHTING IN THIS TRIP.
I CAN TELL YOU, HE'S NOT
HIGHLIGHTING THOSE RECENT POLLS.
I SPOKE TO HIS CHIEF OF STAFF
ABOUT AN HOUR AGO.
FOR EVERY POLL THAT I WAS ABLE
TO MENTION THAT SANDERS WAS
DOWN, HE WAS ABLE TO THROW BACK
POLLS SHOWING SANDERS GAINING
MOMENTUM OR STANDARDS.
HE'S FOCUSING ON RETAIL
POLITICS.
HE'S HAVING ICE CREAM SOCIALS.
HE'S GOING TO BE MARCHING IN, I
THINK, FIVE INDEPENDENCE DAY
PARADES OVER THE COURSE OF THIS
TRIP.
HE'S VYING TO FOCUS ON VOTERS
AND HIS GROUND GAME.
HE JUST OPENED UP AN OFFICE IN
IOWA CITY.
HE'S GOING TO BE OPENING UP TWO
MORE ON THE TRIP, TRYING TO
GALVANIZE SUPPORTERS AND
BRINGING IN AS MUCH AS HE CAN.
>> THAT ORGANIZATION I WILL
ABSOLUTELY BUY BUT I DO NOT
RECOGNIZE THE ICE CREAM SOCIAL
CANDIDATE BERNIE SANDERS
COMPARED TO THE LARGE RALLY
VERSION OF HIM OF 2017.
>> AND SELFIES.
>> ALI, YOU'RE COVERING
ELIZABETH WARREN.
SHE SEEMS TO BE HAVING SOMETHING
OF A MOMENT.
WHAT'S THE SENSE WHERE HER
SUPPORT IS COMING FROM?
IS IT COMING FROM BERNIE
SUPPORTERS?
IS IT COMING FROM ELSEWHERE?
AND HOW DO THEY MAKE SURE THEY
CONTINUE THAT SLOW AND STEADY
BUILD?
>> Reporter: YOU SAY SLOW AND
STEADY, THAT'S BEEN THE MANTRA
HERE.
THEY'VE HELD TO THE THEORY THAT
THE POLLS WILL RISE AND FALL BUT
THE ULTIMATE THING YOU CAN'T GET
BACK IN A CAMPAIGN IS TIME.
THAT'S WHY ELIZABETH WARREN WAS
ONE OF THE EARLIEST PEOPLE IN
THE RACE TO LAUNCH THEY ARE
CAMPAIGN.
SHE'S BEEN GETTING FOLKS OUT ON
THE GROUND.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN HER QUARTER TWO
RATE.
HER BURN GAME IS SO HIGH BECAUSE
THEY INVESTED SO HEAVILY IN THE
GROUND GAME.
WHERE HE'S GOING TO BE IN RENO
TONIGHT, SHE'S SEEN THE PAYOFF.
VOTERS WHO LIKE HER ON POLICY
RECOGNIZE THERE MIGHT BE A
POLICY TWIN IN BERNIE SANDERS.
BUT THEY'RE NOT BUYING HIM AS
THE MESSENGER NECESSARILY.
LISTEN TO WHAT ONE VOTER TOLD ME
LAST NIGHT.
>> BERNIE IS NOT ON MY LIST THIS
TIME AROUND.
I THINK WE ALL HEARD HIS PLANS
LAST TIME.
AND IT DIDN'T GET HIM THE
NOMINATION.
I THINK WE'RE READY FOR SOMEONE
NEW.
AND WHEN I WATCHED THE DEBATES,
BERNIE, TO ME, PERSONALLY, HE
CAME ACROSS AS KIND OF ANGRY AND
IN YOUR FACE.
AND THAT'S NOT WHAT WE NEED
RIGHT NOW.
I'M DONE WITH IN YOUR FACE.
>> Reporter: THIS IS THE REALITY
OF THE NEW LANDSCAPE FOR BERNIE
SANDERS.
LAST TIME AROUND IT WAS HIM
VERSUS HILLARY CLINTON.
THIS TIME AROUND, IT'S HIM AND
HIS IDEAS WITH CENTRAL FOCUS.
BUT MAYBE A LOT CAN PICK UP
WHERE BERNIE SANDERS LEFT OFF,
KASIE.
>> INTERESTING COMMENTS FROM
THAT VOTER THERE.
GINGER GIBSON, THE SANDERS
CAMPAIGN INSISTS THEY'RE GOING
TO TRY TO KEEP THEIR BASE AND
REACH OUT TO DISILLUSIONED
VOTERS.
PERHAPS PEOPLE WHO VOTED FOR
TRUMP TO GET AHEAD IN THE
CAMPAIGN.
THE REALITY IS, HE SEEMS TO BE
BASICALLY IF NOT FALLING, BUT
RIGHT WHERE HE WAS, AND IN A
CROWDED PLAN LIKE THIS, THAT'S A
BAD SPOT TO BE?
>> WHERE IS HIS FLOOR, PEOPLE
HAVE SUGGESTED HE MIGHT ALREADY
BE THERE.
THIS IS HE'S STRIDNT SUPPORTERS
AND HE HASN'T GROWN FROM THERE.
HE HASN'T APPEARED TO EVOLVE OR
GROW HIS BASE IN A WAY THAT
WOULD BRING MORE PEOPLE IN,
PARTICULARLY WHEN THERE ARE MORE
PEOPLE ON THE STAGE WITH HIM OF
WHICH TO CHOOSE FROM.
THE PARTY HAS CHANGED A LOT IN
THE LAST FOUR YEARS.
THE VOTERS HAVE CHANGED A LOT IN
LARGELY, BERNIE SANDERS WILL
TELL YOU, OH, HE'S GOT NEW
PROPOSALS.
HE'S CHANGED A LOT.
REALLY, THE BERNIE SANDERS WE
SAW ON THAT 2016 STAGE IS THE
SAME BERNIE SANDERS WE SAW LAST
WEEK.
>> HE'LL TALK ABOUT ECONOMIC
JUSTICE BUT NOT NECESSARILY
SOCIAL JUSTICE WHICH IS WHAT A
LOT OF VOTERS ARE LOOKING FOR.
>> THANK YOU GUYS VERY MUCH.
>>> THE STAGE IS SET AND THE
TANKS HAVE TAKEN TO THE MALL.
THE CONCERN OVER THE PRESIDENT'S
FOURTH OF JULY SALUTE TO AMERICA
IS ONLY GROWING ACROSS D.C.
THE REASONS WHY, COMING UP NEXT.
I switched to MiraLAX
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives
forcefully stimulate
the nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX works with
the water in your
body to unblock your
system naturally.
And it doesn't cause
bloating,
cramping, gas,
or sudden urgency.
MiraLAX.
Look for the pink cap.
People say if you have
occasional constipation,
you should know the location of
a decent bathroom.
My gut says, take NEW Benefiber
Healthy Balance.
This daily supplement
helps maintain digestive health
naturally
while relieving occasional
constipation
and abdominal discomfort.
NEW Benefiber Healthy Balance
>>> TOMORROW IS THE BIG DAY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S CONTROVERSIAL
SALUTE TO AMERICA.
SOME BRADLEY FIGHTING VEHICLES
SPOTTED HEADING TOWARD THE MALL
BUT THEY'RE NOT THE ONLY THING
ON THE MOVE.
ACCORDING TO "THE WASHINGTON
POST," THE NATIONAL PARK SERVICE
IS DIVERTING $2.5 MILLION FOR
RECREATION FEES PRIMARILY
INTENDED TO IMPROVE PARKS ACROSS
THE COUNTRY, JUST A FRACTION OF
THE EXTRA COST THE GOVERNMENT
FACES AS A RESULT OF THIS EVENT.
THE PRESIDENT PROMISING A SHOW
OF A LIFETIME DEFENDED HIS
PRODUCTION ON TWITTER SAYING,
QUOTE, THE COST OF OUR GREAT
SALUTE TO AMERICA WILL BE VERY
LITTLE COMPARED TO WHAT IT'S
WORTH, WE HAVE THE TANKS AND THE
PILOT, THE AIRPORT IS RIGHT NEXT
DOOR ALL WE NEED IS THE FUEL.
WE OWN THE TANKS AND ALL.
FIREWORKS ARE DONATED.
YOU'RE WATCHING ALL OF THIS
UNFOLD.
AND CLEARLY, ONE OF THE BIG
DIFFERENCES FROM YEARS PAST,
SUDDENLY, THERE IS A VIP
SECTION, FOR THE BEST SEATS IN
THE HOUSE, THAT, YOU KNOW, IT
USED TO BE, WHOEVER -- THE
EGALITARIAN RULE OF THE DAY,
FIRST COME, FIRST SERVED?
>> THAT'S RIGHT, KASIE, EXACTLY.
AS YOU SEE OVER MY SHOULDER,
THOSE PREPS CONTINUE.
WE'RE ACTUALLY GOING TO SHOW YOU
EXACTLY WHERE PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
GOING TO SPEAKING FROM TOMORROW
EVENING.
AS YOU CAN SEE, THE CUSTOMARY
BULLETPROOF CLASS THAT SURROUNDS
THE PRESIDENT AT A LARGE-SCALE
EVENT.
THIS IS OPEN AND FREE TO THE
PUBLIC BUT CERTAINLY THOSE WHO
HAVE TICKETS FROM THE REPUBLICAN
NATIONAL COMMITTEE AND EVEN THE
TRUMP CAMPAIGN HAVE THE BEST
SEATS IN THE HOUSE.
THOSE FOLKS HAVE A PRIMARY
SECTION IN THE FRONT.
AND THEY'LL ACTUALLY HAVE VERY
GOOD VIEW OF SOME OF THOSE
MILITARY VEHICLES.
YOU MENTIONED.
THERE IS A BRADLEY FIGHTING
VEHICLE THAT WAS PARKED ON
INDEPENDENCE AND MOVED HERE A
SHORT TIME AGO.
JUST A SMALL FRACTION OF THE
MILITARY MIGHT THAT WILL BE ON
FULL DISPLAY.
THAT'S WHAT THE PRESIDENT WANTS.
HE WANTS THESE OPTICS AROUND THE
WORLD.
HE WAS INSPIRED IN PARIS BY
PRESIDENT MACRON AND SAID I
WOULD LIKE TO DO THIS BACK HOME.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH THIS IS
GOING TO COST.
THERE ARE A LOT OF ELEMENTS.
MILITARY FLYOVERS.
ALL OF THE MILITARY BRANCHES
REPRESENTED.
AND THE BIG QUESTION WILL THIS
TURN MORE CAMPAIGN RALLY THAN A
TYPICALLY NONPARTISAN EVENT.
THAT REMAINS TO BE SEEN.
THERE ARE SOUND CHECKS HERE.
THEY'RE GETTING READY.
YEAH, SECURITY HAS BEEN TIGHT.
THERE AREN'T TOURISTS ALLOWED
INSIDE THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL
ANYMORE, AND PROBABLY UNTIL THIS
EVENT IS OVER TOMORROW.
THIS TAKING CENTER STAGE ON THE
NATIONAL MALL, KASIE.
>> COURTNEY, TO PICK UP ON THAT
POINT THAT MONICA WAS MAKING AT
THE RISK OF IT TURNING INTO A
CAMPAIGN RALLY.
FIRST OF ALL, HOW UNUSUAL IS IT
FOR THE UNITED STATES MILITARY
TO BE INVOLVED IN A PRODUCTION
LIKE THIS?
HOW MUCH HISTORICALLY IS THIS
SOMETHING THEY'RE USED TO DOING?
AND SECOND OF ALL, WHAT IS THE
LEVEL OF CONCERN AROUND THE
POSSIBILITY OF POLITICS TO PLAY
INTO AN EVENT -- OBVIOUSLY, WE
KNOW OUR MILITARY LEADERS ARE
TYPICALLY TO CLEAR THAT.
>> SO, OF COURSE, THE MILITARY
IS NOT ALLOWED TO BE INVOLVED
OFFICIALLY IN ANY POLITICAL
EVENT.
THERE ARE SPECIFIC RULES.
CANDIDLY IN THE LAST YEAR OR
TWO, WE'VE SEEN MORE GUIDELINES
IN THE LAST COUPLE OF WEEKS,
SECRETARY SHANAHAN PUT OUT A
MEMO REMINDING PEOPLE THAT THE
MILITARY IS APOLITICAL.
FOURTH OF JULY IS NOT TYPICALLY
A MILITARY HOLIDAY WHERE YOU SEE
MILITARY LEADERS SPREAD
THROUGHOUT THE COUNTRY INVOLVED
IN THESE KIND OF ACTIVITIES.
SINCE THE PARADE, THE FIRST OF
THE PLANNING, WHEN WE FIRST
HURTS MENTION OF THE PARADE
THERE HAS BEEN CONCERN FROM
MILITARY LEADERS HERE AT THE
PENTAGON THAT THIS COULD BECOME
A POLITICAL RALLY THAT WOULD BE
AWKWARD FOR THE MILITARY LEADERS
THERE AND THE MILITARY INVOLVED.
DEFENSE OFFICIALS WE'VE SPOKEN
WITH THIS WEEK THAT THEY'RE
ASSURED THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP,
HIS SPEECH IS LESS THAN 20
MINUTES.
HE WILL SPEAK ABOUT FOUR MINUTES
ABOUT EACH SERVICE.
THERE'S SOME BELIEF THAT HE
WANTS THE JOINT CHIEFS -- FOR
THE MOST PART IT WILL BE VICE
CHIEFS WHO WILL BE HERE.
THAT HE WANTS EACH INDIVIDUAL
REPRESENTATIVE AT SOME POINT TO
COME UP AND STAND WITH THEM WHEN
THEY'RE REVIEWING THEIR
AIRCRAFT.
WHEN HE'S TALKING ABOUT THEM OR
WHATEVER.
BUT THERE IS SOME CONCERN THAT
IN FACT THAT COULD LOOK LIKE A
POLITICAL STATEMENT OR A
POLITICAL RALLY.
BUT WHAT'S IMPORTANT TO NOTE
HERE IS THAT THE PENTAGON
LAWYERS, THEY WENT THROUGH THIS
EVENT AS THEY DO WHEN THERE'S
ANY MILITARY PARTICIPATION IN AN
EVENT, THEY FOUND THAT IN FACT
IT IS LEGAL.
AND THEY ARE ALLOWED TO BOTH
PARTICIPATE AND ATTEND THIS
EVENT, KASIE.
>> SO, HAS THE PENTAGON REVIEWED
THE PRESIDENT'S REMARKS?
DO THEY KNOW WHAT HE'S GOING TO
SAY TO MAKE SURE THEY'RE
COMFORTABLE HAVING THEIR GUYS
STAND UP NEXT TO HIM?
>> AT THIS POINT, ALL THEY'VE
BEEN GIVEN IS THE GUIDANCE THAT
HE'LL BE SPEAKING ABOUT THE
VARIOUS SERVICES HERE.
ASSUMING THE WEATHER HOLDS OUT
AND THEY HAVE FLYOVERS EACH WILL
BE REPRESENTED IN THE AIR SHOW.
THE F-22s, THE F-35s.
THE BLUE ANGELS IT WILL
CULMINATE WITH WITH THE NAVY'S
BLUE ANGELS.
OF COURSE, THEY PARTICIPATE IN
AIR SHOWS ALL OVER THE COUNTRY,
ALL OVER THE WORLD SO THAT WON'T
BE UNCOMMON.
WHAT WE DON'T KNOW YET EXACTLY
WILL THE PRESIDENT STICK TO THE
SCRIPT HERE OR GO OFF ON A
POLITICAL TANGENT.
>> ALWAYS AN IMPORTANT QUESTION.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> TODAY, THE COUNTRY SAID
FAREWELL TO A HERO.
ONE MORE TIME UP NEXT.
>>> ONE MORE THING BEFORE WE GO.
TODAY IN NEW YORK, THE CITY AND
WORLD SAID GOOD-BYE TO 9/11
FIRST RESPONDERS LUIS ALVAREZ.
CHANCES ARE YOU KNOW THE NYPD
DETECTIVE FROM HIS FINAL DAYS
SPENT ON CAPITOL HILL, FIGHTING
FOR LAWMAKERS TO CONTINUE
FUNDING FOR THE 9/11
COMPENSATION FUND.
BUT ALVAREZ BECAME AN AMERICAN
HERO LONG BEFORE THEN, ATOP THE
RUBBLE OF GROUND ZERO SPENDING
MONTHS COMBING FOR SURVIVORS AND
REMAINS.
MANY OF HIS FALLEN COMRADES.
DESPITE HAVING TROUBLE BREATHING
DETECTIVE ALVAREZ KEPT GOING
AFTER THE EPA TOLD HIM THE AIR
WAS FINE BUT IT WASN'T.
THREE YEARS AGO, ALVAREZ BEGAN
HIS FIGHT WITH COLON CANCER.
DESPITE GROWING WEAK AND WEAK,
HE NEVER STOPPED FIGHTING.
>> YOU MADE ME COME DOWN HERE
THE DAY BEFORE MY 69th ROUND OF
CHEMO.
AND I'M GOING TO MAKE SURE THAT
YOU NEVER FORGET TO TAKE CARE OF
THE 9/11 RESPONDERS.
IF I CAN HELP, JUST ONE MORE
FIRST RESPONDER, THEN IT MAKES
IT ALL WORTH WHILE FOR ME.
YOU KNOW, IT SOUNDS LIKE A
CLICHE, BUT IT'S THE TRUTH.
>> SADLY, ALVAREZ NEVER MADE IT
TO THAT 69th ROUND OF CHEMO.
INSTEAD GOING INTO HOSPICE,
SHORTLY AFTER HE RETURNED FROM
CAPITOL HILL.
HE PASSED AWAY THIS WEEKEND,
JOINING MORE THAN 2,000 FIRST
RESPONDERS TO PASS AWAY FROM
ILLNESSES RELATED TO THEIR WORK
AT GROUND ZERO.
AT TODAY'S CEREMONY, IN THE SAME
CHURCH HE GREW UP ATTENDING
AFTER MOVING FROM CUBA AT
1-YEAR-OLD, HIS PRIEST RELAYED
THE SINGLE REQUEST THAT LUIS HAD
FOR THIS FUNERAL THAT WE ALL
REMEMBER THE BRAVE MEN AND WOMEN
WHO WENT BEFORE HIM AND THOSE
CONTINUE TO FIGHT NOUN THAT HE'S
GONE.
TODAY AS THE 53-YEAR-OLD WAS
REMEMBERED, THE LAST WORDS HE'S
KNOWN TO HAVE SAID WERE RECITED.
QUOTE, AT THE END, THE ONLY
THING THAT MATTERS IS HOW MUCH
WE LOVED.
MAY HE REST IN PEACE.
THAT WRAPS THINGS UP FOR US THIS
HOUR.
I'