.
>>> THAT WRAPS IT UP FOR US THIS
HOUR ON MSNBC% I'M RICHARD LUI.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
SEE YOU NEXT SATURDAY AT 4:00
P.M.
YOU CAN FOLLOW ME ON FACEBOOK
AND TWITTER.
NOW I TURN IT OVER TO REVEREND
AL SHARPTON AND
"POLITICSNATION."
>>> GOOD EVENING AND WELCOME TO
TONIGHT'S LEDE, PAUL MANAFORT
RECEIVES LESS JAIL TIME THAN
THOUSANDS OF AMERICA'S
NONVIOLENT PRISONERS FOR
DEFRAUDING THE NATION TO THE
TUNE OF MILLIONS.
AND FOR THAT, JUST 47 MONTHS.
LESS THAN FOUR YEARS.
THAT WAS THE RULING FROM A
FEDERAL JUDGE IN VIRGINIA WHERE
HE WAS SENTENCED THURSDAY FOR
FINANCIAL FRAUD, NOT FOR
ALLEGEDLY CONSPIRING WITH
FOREIGN AGENTS.
A DISTINCTION THE JUDGE THE
VIRGINIA EMPHASIZED SUNDAY.
SO PRESIDENT TRUMP MISSED THE
POINT TWEETING FRIDAY, QUOTE,
BOTH THE JUDGE AND THE LAWYER IN
THE PAUL MANAFORT CASE STATED
LOUDLY AND FOR THE WORLD TO HEAR
THERE WAS NO COLLUSION WITH
RUSSIA.
BUT WHILE WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
DESPERATELY CONTROLLING THE
MEDIA NARRATIVE, THE PRESIDENT
LOST YET ANOTHER COMMUNICATIONS
DIRECTOR THIS WEEK.
FORMER FOX NEWS EXECUTIVE BILL
SHINE, JUST AS HE'S GEARING UP
FOR HIS RE-ELECTION CAMPAIGN,
WHICH WILL BE EXECUTED BY HALF
OF MY PANEL TONIGHT WHO JOINS ME
FROM DALLAS, KATRINA PEARSON.
AND WITH ME HERE ON SET, DAVID
BROCK, CHAIRMAN OF AMERICAN
BRIDGE 21st CENTURY.
LET ME GO TO YOU FIRST, KATRINA.
THE PRESIDENT IS CLEARLY OFF ON
HIS FACTS WHEN HE SAYS THAT, YOU
KNOW, THIS JUDGE AND EVERYONE IS
SAYING HE'S CLEARED OF RUSSIAN
COLLUSION.
THIS WAS NOT ABOUT THAT.
THAT WOULD BE WEDNESDAY.
BUT THE PRESIDENT HAS HAD A KIND
OF ROUGH WEEK FROM MICHAEL COHEN
TO NOW BILL SHINE, HIS
COMMUNICATION DIRECTOR LEAVING.
AND WE SEE OTHER THINGS ON THE
HORIZON.
IS BILL SHINE'S RESIGNATION A
RESULT OF THE CONTINUING MEDIA
ATTENTION ON THIS CONNECTION
BETWEEN FOX NEWS AND THE
PRESIDENT, THE HEIGHT OF WHICH
WAS THE "NEW YORKER" MAGAZINE
PIECE THAT REALLY OUTLINED IN
VERY, VERY GRAPHIC DETAILS HOW
FOX NEWS HAS COVERED AND REALLY
BECOME JUST TOTALLY DONALD
TRUMP'S TELEVISION.
>> GOOD EVENING, REVEREND AND
THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
THERE'S A LOT OF THINGS I WOULD
LIKE TO UNPACK, FIRST YOU
STARTED WITH THE MANAFORT
SENTENCING AND THE PRESIDENT'S
STATING EXACTLY WHAT THE JUDGE
SAID.
IT WAS A REMINDER TO EVERYONE
THAT THIS HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
THE RUSSIA COLLUSION HOAX, AND I
THINK IT'S VERY IMPORTANT --
>> NO IT HAD NOTHING -- THE
SENTENCING ON THAT CASE HAD
NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
THE PRESIDENT SAID THAT THE
JUDGE SAID --
>> NOR THE CHARGES.
>> WAIT A MINUTE, I'LL LET YOU
TALK THEN YOU LET ME TALK.
HE SAID THAT THE SENTENCING HAD
NOTHING TO DO -- HE DID NOT SAY
THERE WAS NO RUSSIAN COLLUSION.
>> THE JUDGE DID SPECIFICALLY
STATE THAT THIS ENTIRE CASE HAD
NOTHING TO DO WITH COLLUSION OR
RUSSIA.
>> THAT'S WHAT I JUST SAID.
>> SO IT'S WORTH NOTING AND
STATING BECAUSE WHAT WE'VE SEEN
IN THIS MANIC REACTION TO THE
SENTENCING REFORM.
YOU HAD ELECTED OFFICIALS ON
THIS NETWORK SAYING THAT PAUL
MANAFORT IS SOMEHOW AN ENEMY OF
THE STATE AND HOW HE PERPETUATED
AN ATROCITY AGAINST A DEMOCRACY.
>> WE WILL SEE THE SENTENCING ON
THAT ON WEDNESDAY.
>> THAT'S MY POINT, REVEREND,
THERE NO SENTENCING ON
COLLUSION.
THERE ARE NO RUSSIA COLLUSION
CHARGES TO BE SENTENCED.
>> WELL, I THINK ON WEDNESDAY
WHEN HE IS SENTENCED AND GOING
FORWARD WE WILL SEE WHAT THAT
JUDGE SAYS AND WE WILL SEE WHAT
COMES OUT OF THESE RUSSIAN
COLLUSION INVESTIGATIONS.
THAT IS NOT -- THAT'S FAR FROM
OVER.
BUT AGAIN, THE PRESIDENT WAS
INCORRECT IN HIS SAYING THAT THE
JUDGE SAID THERE IS NO RUSSIAN
COLLUSION.
THERE WAS NONE IN THAT CASE.
BUT YOU ARE AVOIDING MY QUESTION
ON BILL SHINE AND THE CONNECTION
WITH FOX NEWS AND WHETHER IT WAS
CONNECTED WITH "NEW YORKER."
YOU'RE VERY TRUMPIAN, YOU ARE
AVOIDING THE ISSUE.
>> NO, I'M ACTUALLY NOT.
I JUST WANTED TO TAKE EACH ONE
CASE BY CASE.
>> BUT I ONLY ASKED ONE
QUESTION.
LET'S DEAL WITH THE QUESTION OF
BILL SHINE.
>> I THINK THAT IT'S FALSE TO
SAY THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS LOST
BILL SHINE.
BILL SHINE IS SIMPLY
TRANSFERRING TO THE CAMPAIGN.
THIS IS NOT UNCOMMON WHEN IT
COMES TO HIGH-PROFILE
INDIVIDUALS IN A WHITE HOUSE
GOING TO THE CAMPAIGN.
DAVID AXELROD DID IT IN 2012.
JAMES BAKER STEPPED DOWN AS
SECRETARY OF STATE TO LEAD
GEORGE W. BUSH'S EFFORTS.
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH FOX
NEWS OR ANY INVESTIGATION
SURROUNDING THE WHITE HOUSE
BECAUSE THERE ARE PLENTY YOU CAN
CHOOSE FROM.
HE HASN'T LOST ANYTHING BECAUSE
BILL SHINE WILL BE VERY MUCH
ENGAGED IN PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
ORBIT AS WELL AS WITH THE
RE-ELECTION CAMPAIGN.
>> DAVID, I THINK WHAT IS
DIFFERED, THOUGH, ABOUT AXELROD
AND OTHERS IS I DON'T THINK ANY
PRESIDENT IN TWO AND A HALF
YEARS HAD AS MANY COMMUNICATIONS
DIRECTORS COME AND GO AS THIS
PRESIDENT HAS.
AND THAT IS PROBABLY THE
DIFFERENCE.
NOR DO I THINK YOU'VE HAD THIS
WILD KIND OF ASSOCIATION OF ONE
NETWORK WITH ONE PRESIDENT AT
THE TIME THAT SHINE RESIGNED WAS
THE TIME THIS "NEW YORKER" PIECE
WAS REALLY BEING TALKED ABOUT.
>> RIGHT.
I DON'T THINK IT'S A COINCIDENCE
THAT THE "NEW YORKER" CAME OUT
THIS WEEK AND SHOWED THAT WHAT
WE'VE ALL KNOWN FOR A LONG TIME
THAT FOX NEWS IS A PROPAGANDA
OUTLET.
IT IS NIGHT AND DAY RELENTLESS
PRO-TRUMP, THAT THE PRESIDENT
GETS HIS TALKING POINTS FROM FOX
NEWS IN THE MORNING AND THERE'S
AN INSIDIOUS FEEDBACK LOOP.
I DON'T KNOW HOW SIGNIFICANT IT
IS, IT COULD BE THAT SHINE'S
ROLL WITH THE FOX CONNECTION
BECAME SUPERFLUOUS BECAUSE
RUPERT MURDOCK IS TALKING
REGULARLY AND SEAN HANNITY IS
TALKING TO DONALD TRUMP.
AND THAT'S NOT JOURNALISM, REV.
>> SINCE YOU ARE NOW, KATRINA,
DEALING WITH THE RE-ELECTION,
THE PRESIDENT TALKED ABOUT HOW
HE WAS GOING TO DO ALL THESE
THINGS IN TERMS OF THE DEFICIT,
IN TERMS OF THE ECONOMY, AND YET
WE ARE SEEING RECORD DEFICIT.
I'M GOING TO DEAL WITH THAT
LATER IN THE SHOW, $891 BILLION
TRADE DEFICIT.
HOW DO YOU RUN FOR RE-ELECTION
WHEN HE'S DONE THE EXACT
OPPOSITE OF WHAT HE PROMISED THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE, INCLUDING HIS
BASE?
>> WELL, FIRST LET ME JUST SAY
THAT THAT NO ONE AT FOX NEWS WAS
GIVING DONALD TRUMP DEBATE
QUESTIONS.
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THE
DEFICIT NOW.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT -- KATRINA,
KATRINA.
ONE OF THE THINGS WE'RE GOING TO
DO ON THIS SHOW IS WE'RE GOING
TO DEFICIT.
A DEFICIT.
HE RAN THAT HE COULD MANAGE THE
DEFICIT, HE ATTACKED HIS
PREDECESSORS ABOUT THE DEFICIT.
HOW DO YOU RUN FOR RE-ELECTION
WHEN YOU'VE DONE THE TOTAL
OPPOSITE OF WHAT YOU PROMISED,
PEOPLE INCLUDING YOUR BASE.
THAT'S THE QUESTION.
>> LOOK, REVEREND, IT'S NOT THE
TOTAL OPPOSITE.
I MEAN, THE PRESIDENT'S BEEN IN
OFFICE FOR TWO YEARS NOW.
AND I THINK IT'S SAFE TO SAY
THAT TRADE DEFICITS, FOR
EXAMPLE, HAVE BEEN AN EXTREME
PROBLEM, AND THIS IS ONE
PRESIDENT THAT HAS PUT AMERICA
FIRST WHEN IT COMES TO
RENEGOTIATING TRADE AGREEMENTS.
WHAT WE DO SEE HAPPENING IS
RECORD NUMBER OF JOBS COMING
BACK INTO THE UNITED STATES.
WE SEE UNEMPLOYMENT AS AN
ALL-TIME LOW.
WE SEE AFRICAN-AMERICAN
UNEMPLOYMENT HISTORICALLY AT
LOWER LEVELS BECAUSE HE IS
EMPOWERING THE ECONOMY BY BY
TAKING ON --
>> UNEMPLOYMENT WAS GOING DOWN
BEFORE HE CAME IN AND IT JUST
CONTINUED.
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH THE
FACT THAT HE PROMISED HE WAS
GOING TO TAKE CONTROL OF THE
DEFICIT.
THE DEFICIT, DAVID, IS HIGHER
THAN IT HAS BEEN, AND HE IS THE
ONE, NOT HIS OPPONENTS OR HIS
CRITICS, THAT SAID HE WOULD
MANAGE AND DEAL WITH IT.
THAT HAS NOT NOT HAPPENED.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
HE CAME INTO OFFICE SAYING WITH
HIS CREDENTIAL THAT HE WAS A
BUSINESSMAN.
HE SAID HE WOULD SOLVE THIS
PROBLEM OF THE DEFICIT.
WE ARE GOING TO HAVE A
BALLOONING DEFICIT WE'LL HAVE TO
PAY FOR, WE'RE GOING TO PAY THE
PRICE AT SOME POINT.
AND IT'S ANOTHER EXAMPLE OF
DONALD TRUMP BETRAYING
CONSERVATIVE PRINCIPLES TIME AND
AGAIN.
THIS IS USUALLY A CONSERVATIVE
ISSUE.
AND HE'S LOST ON IT.
TIME AND AGAIN FROM BETRAYING
OUR ALLIES, THIS PRESIDENT HAS
NO IDEOLOGICAL CORE.
>> WHAT HAPPENED IN NORTH KOREA,
KATRINA?
NOTHING HAPPENED.
THE PRESIDENT GAVE ONE VERSION,
THE NORTH KOREANS GAVE ANOTHER
VERSION.
CAN YOU SHARE WITH US WHAT YOU
KNOW IF YOU KNOW?
>> I CAN JUST SHARE WITH YOU
WHAT I THINK.
WE HAVE NOT HAD THIS DISCUSSION
AT THE CAMPAIGN.
THAT IS A WHITE HOUSE QUESTION.
BUT I WILL ALSO SAY THANK YOU
AND I'M VERY GLAD THAT DEMOCRATS
ARE NOW SUDDENLY CONCERNED WITH
THE DEFICIT.
BUT WITH REGARDS TO NORTH KOREA,
IT'S VERY TELLING THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP DURING THE CAMPAIGN
PROMISED THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
THAT HE WOULD DO WHATEVER IT
TOOK TO TRY AND RESOLVE THESE
MAJOR ISSUES AROUND THE WORLD,
NORTH KOREA BEING ONE OF THEM.
OF COURSE WE EXPECT NORTH KOREA
TO GIVE THEIR OWN VERSION OF
THINGS.
I DON'T THINK ANYONE IS
SURPRISED THAT THEY HAVE THEIR
OWN PROPAGANDA THAT THEY PUSH
OUT.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, MANY
AMERICANS ARE ACTUALLY PLEASED
THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP IS ACTUALLY
TRYING TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE IN
ENDING THE WAR IN KOREA AND
BRINGING BACK OUR SOLDIERS.
IT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN
OVERNIGHT.
>> BUT I THOUGHT THEY HAD THIS
GREAT LOVE AFFAIR AND THEY HAD
THIS GREAT KIND OF BONDING GOING
ON.
YET HE WAS NOT ABLE TO MOVE THE
MARK AND THERE ARE EVEN REPORTS,
INCLUDING VIDEO, THAT THEY ARE
NOW REBUILDING THEIR NUCLEAR
PLAN WHERE THEY HAD PROMISED
THAT THEY WERE, IN MANY WAYS,
BRINGING DOWN OR TRYING TO --
PRESIDENT AND OTHERS WERE
LEADING US TO BELIEVE THAT THERE
WAS MOVING TOWARD THEIR
DENUCLEARIZING AND IT SEEMS LIKE
THE OPPOSITE IS HAPPENING NOW.
>> THAT'S APPARENTLY WHAT IT
MIGHT SEEM LIKE IF YOU BELIEVE
THE MEDIA, BUT I ALSO BELIEVE
OUR STATE DEPARTMENT AND THE
PRESIDENT, AND I BELIEVE THAT IN
GOOD FAITH THINGS ARE MOVING --
>> WHEN YOU SEE VIDEO OF THEM --
>> THINGS ARE MOVING FORWARD.
>> BUT WHEN YOU SEE, DAVID,
THERE ARE VIDEOS SHOWING WHERE
THE ACTUAL NUCLEAR SITE IS BEING
REDEVELOPED, THIS IS NOT MEDIA.
>> IT'S NOT.
>> AND NORTH KOREA WILL NOT
SAY -- THEY'RE NOT DENYING THAT
THEY HAVE NOT ENTERED INTO ANY
KIND OF DENUCLEARIZATION, SO
THIS IS NOT ABOUT THE MEDIA.
>> IT'S NOT ABOUT THE MEDIA AT
ALL.
IT'S ABOUT OUR INTELLIGENCE AND
PROOF.
THE PRESIDENT MAY NOT RESPECT
OUR INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES, BUT
THE AMERICAN PUBLIC DOES.
WHAT WE SEE TIME AND AGAIN IS
DIPLOMACY WHERE TRUMP THINKS HE
CAN COZY UP TO THESE OWEDOUS
DICTATORS AND HE COMES UP EMPTY
HANDED TIME AND AGAIN.
>> KATRINA AND DAVID, DON'T GO
AWAY.
>>> COMING UP FIRST, 14, THAT'S
THE NUMBER OF DEMOCRATS WHO ARE
OFFICIALLY RUNNING FOR 2020
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION, ONE OF
THEM IS JOINING US NEXT.
BE RIGHT BACK.
T.
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it from
your allergy pills?
Most pills don't
finish the job
because they don't relieve
nasal congestion.
Flonase Sensimist
is different.
It relieves all
your worst symptoms,
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
It's more complete
allergy relief.
And all from a gentle mist
you can barely feel.
Flonase Sensimist helps block
six key inflammatory
substances.
Most pills only block one.
And six is
greater than one.
Flonase Sensimist.
Mom! He's Blinking too loud.
Sorry, is that too loud?ix is
greater than one.
You don't need any more hormones
in your house.
That's why you chose Kraft
Natural Cheese.
Made with fresh milk without the
added hormone rbST.
It's Cheese as it should be.
This is not a bed...
it's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed, from $999...
senses your movement and
automatically adjusts
on each side to keep
you both comfortable.
And snoring?
How smart is that?
Smarter sleep.
So you can come out swinging,
maintain your inner
focus, and wake up rested
and ready for anything.
Only at a Sleep Number store,
save $500 on select Sleep
Number 360 smart beds.
Plus, free premium
delivery and setup.
Ends March 17th.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
WE'RE ANTICIPATING MORE
CANDIDATES WILL ANNOUNCE THEY'RE
THEY'RE JOINING THIS CROWDED
FIELD OF DEMOCRATS RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT IN 2020, BUT THIS WEEK
WILL HE WHEN WE LEARNED OF A FEW
BIG NAMES WHO ARE NOT.
MICHAEL BLOOMBERG, THE FORMER
MAYOR OF NEW YORK CITY, ERIC
HOLDER, THE FORMER U.S. ATTORNEY
GENERAL, SENATOR SHARED BROWN OF
OHIO, AND SENATOR JEFF MERKLEY
OF OREGON, OH, AND ADD HILLARY
CLINTON WHO ALSO SAID, QUOTE,
I'M NOT RUNNING TO A NEW YORK
CITY TELEVISION STATION.
BUT BY JUDGING BY THE CANDIDATES
WHO ARE RUNNING, THIS IS A
DEMOCRATIC PARTY DIFFERENT FROM
EVEN THREE YEARS AGO WHEN
CLINTON LAST RAN.
SOME SAY MORE LIBERAL, OTHERS
SAY TOO LIBERAL TO BEAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
JOINING ME IS ONE OF THE
CANDIDATES, FORMER HOUSING
SECRETARY AND FORMER MAYOR OF
SAN ANTONIO, JULIAN CASTRO.
LET ME START BY ASKING YOU, MR.
CASTRO, IN A CROWDED FIELD, HOW
ARE ANY OF THE CANDIDATES
DISTINGUISHING YOURSELVES?
DOES IT MAKE IT WHERE YOU HAVE
TO DO SOMETHING PROVOCATIVE TO
EVEN BE NOTICED, OR DO YOU JUST
RUN YOUR RACE HOPING YOUR
MESSAGE BREAKS THROUGH, EVEN
THOUGH YOU HAVE SO MANY PEOPLE
ON THE STAGE WITH YOU?
>> IT'S GOOD TO BE WITH YOU,
REVEREND AL.
FOR ME I'VE ALWAYS BELIEVED THAT
THE THE FIRST THING THAT YOU
SHOULD DO WHEN YOU'RE RUNNING
FOR OFFICE IS TO TELL PEOPLE
WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO DO FOR THEM
AND THEIR FAMILY IF THEY VOTE
FOR YOU.
IN OTHER WORDS, WHAT YOU WANT TO
DO IF YOU'RE ELECTED.
SO I'M GOING TO GO OUT THERE AND
ARTICULATE A STRONG, POSITIVE
VISION FOR THE COUNTRY'S FUTURE.
I'VE TALKED ABOUT IN THIS 21st
CENTURY MAKING THE UNITED STATES
THE SMARTEST, THE HEALTHIEST,
THE FAIREST, AND THE MOST
PROSPEROUS NATION ON EARTH.
I SEE MYSELF AS THE ANTITHESIS
OF PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HE'S BEEN THE MOST DIVISIVE
PRESIDENT WE'VE HAD IN QUITE A
WHILE.
I'D LIKE TO BRING THE COUNTRY
TOGETHER.
I'VE DEMONSTRATED INTEGRITY AND
HONEST.
I WANT TO BE A PRESIDENT FOR ALL
AMERICANS AND NOT JUST A
PRESIDENT FOR 37% THAT HE SEES
AS HIS BASE.
I'M FUNDAMENTALLY FOCUSED ON THE
FUTURE.
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE THIS
COUNTRY ANYTHING AGAIN, I WANT
TO MAKE IT BETTER THAN EVER FOR
ALL AMERICANS.
>> YOU ARE THE ONLY ANNOUNCED
LATINO IN THE RACE.
CERTAINLY WHEN WE DEAL WITH THE
IDENTITY POLITICS PEOPLE WOULD
YOU SAY THAT DISTINGUISHES YOU,
BUT YOU ALSO SERVED ACROSS
RACIAL AND NATIONALITY LINES AT
HUD, AS MAYOR, SO YOUR MESSAGE
COMES FROM A PLACE THAT YOU
UNDERSTAND BUT HAS GONE TO A
PLACE YOU CLEARLY OUTLINED HERE.
IN YOUR HOME STATE OF TEXAS,
THERE'S A LOT OF EXPLANATION
THAT BETO O'ROURKE MAY RUN, AND
HE'S EVEN AS LATE AS TODAY PUT
OUT PEOPLE SHOULD SIGN UP TO BE
THE FIRST TO KNOW WHAT HE
DECIDES TO DO.
WILL BETO O'ROURKE AFFECT YOUR
CAMPAIGN, BOTH OF YOU COMING
FROM TEXAS, BOTH OF YOU RAISING
MONEY IN TEXAS IF HE WERE TO
RUN, AS MANY OF US FEEL, WILL IT
IMPACT OR ALTER IN ANY WAY YOUR
CAMPAIGN.
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE A VERY CROWDED PRIMARY
ALREADY.
I THINK WE HAVE 14 OR 15
CANDIDATES THAT ARE RUNNING.
I WAS PLEASED TO SUPPORT, HAPPY
TO SUPPORT CONGRESSMAN O'ROURKE
WHEN HE RAN FOR SENATE AGAINST
TED CRUZ.
I THINK HE'S AN IMPRESSIVE
CANDIDATE.
I'M SURE HE'LL BRING HIS VOICE
AND EXPERIENCE TO THE TABLE JUST
LIKE ALL THE OTHER CANDIDATES.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO CHANGE WHAT
I DO.
INS GOING TO CHANGE THE MESSAGE
I'M DELIVERING OR THE EXPERIENCE
I'LL OFFER IF I'M LEAKED
PRESIDENT.
SO I'M JUST GOING TO FOCUS ON
GETTING TO THE VOTERS IN THESE
EARLY STATES AND THROUGHOUT THE
COUNTRY.
I MADE A PLEDGE ABOUT TWO WEEKS
AGO TO VISIT EVERY SINGLE STATE
IN OUR UNION.
I STARTED IN IDAHO AND THEN WENT
TO UTAH, TWO PLACES WHERE
DEMOCRATS DON'T USUALLY GO.
AND I'M GOING TO KEEP DOING
THAT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER IF WE HAVE 40
PEOPLE IN THE RACE.
I'M GOING TO SKETCH OUT MY OWN
VISION FOR THE FUTURE AND LET
THE CHIPS FALL WHERE THEY MAY.
>> MOST PEOPLE POLLED ARE SAYING
THAT -- I'M TALKING MOST
DEMOCRATS, THAT THEY ARE REALLY
WANTING A CANDIDATE THAT CAN
DEFEAT PRESIDENT TRUMP.
YOUR ARRANGEMENT TO THOSE
VOTERS, WHAT YOU FEEL IS THE
MOST EMIGRATION THINGS THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS DONE THAT
YOU WOULD DO DIFFERENTLY OR THE
OPPOSITE OF IF YOU WERE TO BE
ELECTED?
>> I'D SAY TO RESTORE INTEGRITY
AND HONESTY TO THE WHITE HOUSE.
THIS IS A PRESIDENT THAT HAS
BEEN MORE UNTRUTHFUL PROBABLY IN
THE HISTORY OF OUR NATION'S
HISTORY.
PEOPLE HAVE SEEN THE NUMBER OF
LIES HE'S TOLD ABOUT ANY NUMBER
OF THINGS, AND IT'S DAMAGING OUR
DEMOCRACY.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT THE
PEOPLE OF THE UNITED STATES HAVE
A GOVERNMENT THAT THEY CAN TRUST
IN WASHINGTON, D.C.
ON TOP OF THAT, I REALLY BELIEVE
IT'S TIME FOR A PRESIDENT WHO IS
TRYING TO BRING PEOPLE TOGETHER
AND NOT TO TEAR THEM APART.
WE NEED SOMEBODY THAT IS NOT
ONLY, YOU KNOW, FOCUSED ON THE
FUTURE AND HAS A STRONG AGENDA
FOR THE FUTURE, BUT ALSO TRYING
TO WORK WITH THE OTHER SIDE WHEN
IT'S APPROPRIATE, NOT JUST
THROWING INSULTS OUT THERE
EITHER TO PEOPLE WHO ARE IN
ANOTHER PARTY OR TO FOREIGN
LEADERS.
THIS PRESIDENT HAS DAMAGED OUR
DEMOCRACY, AND I WOULD LIKE TO
RETURN US TO A STRONG PATH FOR
GROWTH, FOR PROSPERITY, FOR ALL
AMERICANS IN THE YEARS TO COME.
AND I WOULD SAY ALSO FOR THOSE
WHO WONDER, WELL, HOW ARE YOU
GOING TO BEAT THIS PRESIDENT?
WE'RE NOT GOING TO BE BEAT THIS
PRESIDENT BY TRYING TO BE THIS
PRESIDENT.
WE'RE GOING TO BEAT THIS
PRESIDENT BY OFFERING A STRONG,
POSITIVE VISION FOR THE FUTURE
AND TRYING TO UNITE PEOPLE, AND
FOCUSING ON ALL AMERICANS, NOT
JUST WHAT THIS PRESIDENT DOES,
WHICH IS JUST FOCUS ON 37% THAT
HE CONSIDERS HIS BASE AND IF HE
JUST BRINGS THOSE PEOPLE OUT,
HE'S GOING TO WIN NARROWLY LIKE
HE DID LAST TIME.
HE LOST BY 2.8 MILLION VOTES IN
THE POPULAR VOTE BUT HE THINKS
HE CAN RUN THE TABLE AGAIN WITH
THIS NARROW STRATEGY.
I BELIEVE I CAN GO BACK AND GET
MICHIGAN, WISCONSIN, AND
PENNSYLVANIA.
WE ONLY LOST THEM BY LESS THAN
80,000 VOTES NEXT TIME, AND I'M
CONFIDENT IF I'M THE NOMINEE WE
CAN GET THE 2019 ELECTORAL VOTES
IN FLORIDA, THE 11 ELECTORAL
VOTES OF ARIZONA, AND EVEN THE
38 ELECTORAL VOTES IN TEXAS.
>> YOU CAME OUT THIS WEEK ON THE
LAST SEVERAL WEEKS SUPPORTING
THE IDEA OF LOOKING INTO
REPARATIONS FOR
AFRICAN-AMERICANS.
HOW DO YOU FEEL WE NEED DO DEAL
WITH THOSE SEGMENTS IN THIS
COUNTRY THAT HAVE A
DISPROPORTIONATE -- WE KEEP
TALKING ABOUT HOW THE ECONOMY'S
DOING WELL, BUT IT IS STILL
UNEVEN WHEN IT COMES TO BLACKS
AND LATINOS.
>> WELL, OF COURSE THAT'S TRUE.
WHAT I SAID A COUPLE WEEKS AGO
IS THAT I HAVE LONG BELIEVED
THAT ONE OF THE WAYS WE SHOULD
CONSIDER ADDRESSING THE ORIGINAL
SIN OF SLAVERY IS REPARATIONS.
I ASKED FOLKS, I SAID UNDER OUR
CONSTITUTION WE COMPENSATE
PEOPLE IF WE TAKE THEIR
PROPERTY.
SHOULDN'T PEOPLE BE COMPENSATED
IF THEY WERE PROPERTY?
THAT WAS SANCTIONED BY THE
STATE?
IN THIS CASE, SHOULDN'T BE
COMPENSATE THEIR.
TO FULLY MOVE FORWARD AS ONE
NATION WITH ONE DESTINY THAT
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO ADDRESS
THAT.
AND THE WAY THAT I WOULD DRESS
IT IF I'M ELECTED PRESIDENT IS
BY APPOINTING A COMMISSION OF
PEOPLE, OF DIFFERENT WALKS OF
LIFE WHO UNDERSTAND THIS ISSUE,
A TASK FORCE TO COME UP WITH
ACTION THAT WE CAN TAKE ON
REPARATIONS.
SOME PEOPLE HAVE ASKED, WELL,
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHY ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT A
COMMISSION INSTEAD OF JUST
SAYING YOU'RE GOING TO DO THIS?
AND THE REASON FOR THAT IS
BECAUSE, AS YOU KNOW, THIS IS A
SUBJECT PEOPLE VIEW DIFFERENTLY
AND THERE ARE DIFFERENT WAYS WE
CAN ADDRESS IT.
AT THE END OF IT, WHAT WE WOULD
LIKE IS FOR IT TO BE HEALING FOR
THE COUNTRY.
IN ORDER TO DO THAT, WE HAVE TO
PAY AS MUCH ATTENTION NOT ONLY
TO THE END RESULT, BUT ALSO TO
THE PROCESS TO GET THERE SO THAT
IT CAN BRING AMERICANS TOGETHER
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.
>> ALL RIGHT >> AND I THINK
THAT'S DONE THROUGH A TASK
FORCE.
>> WE ALSO MUST HEAL THE
INJURED.
THANK YOU, JULIAN CASTRO.
AND A NOTE.
IN LESS THAN ONE MONTH THE
NATIONAL ACTION NETWORK WILL
GATHER CIVIL RIGHTS ACTIVISTS,
STAKEHOLDERS, AND 2020
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES FOR THE
28th ANNUAL NATIONAL CONVENTION
TO EXAMINE THE STATE OF CIVIL
LIBERTIES AND RACIAL JUSTICE
TODAY.
AMONG THE SPEAKERS AND
PANELISTS, 2020 PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES, SENATORS CORY
BOOKER, KIRSTEN GILLIBRAND,
KAMALA HARRIS, AMY KLOBUCHAR,
JEFF MERKLEY, BERNIE SANDERS,
ELIZABETH WARREN, MAYOR PETE
BUTTIGIEG, CONGRESSMAN JOHN
DILANIAN, ENTREPRENEUR ANDREW
YANG AND STACY ABRAMS, VALERIE
JARED, ERIC HOLDER, KAREN BASS,
LUCY McBATH, AND ALEXANDRIA
OCASIO-CORTEZ.
AND REVEREND JESSE JACKSON.
GO ONLINE AND REGISTER.
IT'S FREE.
THAT'S APRIL 3rd TO THE 6th IN
NEW YORK CITY.
>>> COMING UP, PRESIDENT TRUMP
HAS COMPLETELY FAILED IN ONE OF
HIS CAMPAIGN PROMISES.
I'LL TELL YOU WHICH ONE NEXT.
At Midas, with every oil change
you get a free tire rotation.
Makes you feel like a king!
King for a day!
Well, maybe not the whole day.
Our 19.99 or 49.99 oil change
includes a tire rotation.
.
>>> I WAS LOOKING AT SOME OF
THOSE BIG, ONCE-INCREDIBLE,
JOB-PRODUCING FACTORIES AND MY
WIFE, MELANIA, SAID WHAT
HAPPENED?
I SAID THOSE JOBS HAVE LEFT
OHIO.
THEY'RE ALL COMING BACK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
COMING BACK.
DON'T MOVE.
DON'T SELL YOUR HOUSE.
>> YEP, TIME FOR MY WEEKLY MEMO
TO PRESIDENT TRUMP.
YOUR AMERICA-FIRST POLICIES ARE
A DISASTER.
AND AMERICANS ARE TIRED OF
PAYING THE PRICE.
YOU KEEP INSISTING WE'RE WINNING
THIS TRADE WAR WITH CHINA AND
THAT TRADE DEFICIT IS DOWN.
WELL, THAT'S A FLATOUT LIE.
THIS WEEK THE U.S. TRADE DEFICIT
IN GOODS HIT A RECORD HIGH OF
$891 BILLION.
THE SAME DAY THAT AUTO MAKER
GENERAL MOTORS ANNOUNCED PLANS
TO CLOSE YET ANOTHER ASSEMBLY
PLANT AND CUTTING NEARLY 1,700
JOBS.
AND BECAUSE YOU TRIED TO GO
AFTER CHINA ALONE INSTEAD OF
BANDING TOGETHER WITH OUR
ALLIES, AMERICAN FARMERS ARE
BEARING THE BRUNT OF YOUR BAD
DECISIONS.
FARMERS ACROSS THE MIDWEST ARE
FILING FOR BANKRUPTCY AT
ALARMING RATES, NOT SEEN IN A
DECADE.
DURING THE CAMPAIGN YOU PROMISED
THAT ELIMINATING OUR NATIONAL
DEBT WOULD BE A PIECE OF CAKE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
NOT ONLY DO WE HAVE A HISTORIC
TRADE DEFICIT, BUT YOU AND
REPUBLICANS WHO RAN CONGRESS FOR
THE PAST TWO YEARS SPENT REAL
BIG AND PASSED TAX CUT PACKAGES
THAT STILL HASN'T BEEN PAID FOR.
NOW YOUR WHITE HOUSE PLANS TO
UNVEIL AN UNBALANCED BUDGET
CALLING FOR MORE SPENDING ON
IMMIGRATION ENFORCEMENT WHILE
SLASHING DOMESTIC PROGRAMS LIKE
FOOD STAMPS AND FARM SUBSIDIES,
I KNOW YOU TRIED TO SEAL YOUR
SCHOOL TRANSCRIPT, BUT IT'S
CLEAR YOU COULDN'T HAVE PASSED
ECONOMICS 101 IF YOU THINK THIS
IS PUTTING AMERICA FIRST.
BE RIGHT BACK.
They're America's
biopharmaceutical researchers.
Driven each day to pursue
life-changing cures...
In a country built on
fostering innovation.
Here, they find breakthroughs...
Like a way to fight cancer by
arming a patient's own
T-cells...
And a new therapy that gives the
blind a working gene
so they can see again.
Because it's not just about
the next breakthrough...
It's all the ones after that.
>>> I THINK THERE HAS TO BE
OPERATIONS AND WE CAN DISCUSS
WHAT THAT IS.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO BE CORRECT
COURSE WITHOUT INTERVENTION SO
WE NEED CONVERSATION ABOUT WHAT
THAT INTERVETION SHOULD LOOK
LIKE.
>> I HAVE LONG BELIEVED THIS
COUNTRY SHOULD RESOLVE ITS
ORIGINAL SIN OF SLAVERY AND ONE
OF THE WAYS WE SHOULD CONSIDER
DOING THAT IS THROUGH
REPARATIONS FOR PEOPLE WHO ARE
THE DISSEN DENTS OF SLAVES.
>> THE TOPIC OF REPARATIONS,
ONCE POLITICAL RETRO ACTIVE,
EVEN FOR DEMOCRATS, HAS FOUND
ITS WAY INTO THE DEBATE WITH
FOUR CANDIDATES ON RECORD AS
ENDORSING SOME RESTITUTION FOR
THE DESCENDANTS OF SAVES.
THE HIGHEST AFRICAN-AMERICAN IN
CONGRESS IS UNCONVINCED.
MAJORITY WHIP JAMES CLYBURN WHO
SAID THIS WEEK THAT, QUOTE, PURE
REPARATIONS WOULD BE IMPOSSIBLE
TO IMPLEMENT.
BACK WITH ME, KATRINA PIERSON,
AND DAVID BROCK, CHAIRMAN OF
AMERICAN BRIDGE 21st CENTURY.
KATRINA, HOW ABOUT IT IS THIS IF
THE CONGRESS PASSED A BILL,
HOUSE AND SENATE, TO STUDY
REPARATIONS, WOULD THE PRESIDENT
SIGN THE BILL?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVEN'T ASKED HIM ABOUT
REPARATIONS, BUT TO YOUR LAST
POINT, IT'S NEARLY IMPOSSIBLE TO
EVEN TRY TO COME UP WITH THE
CRITERIA FOR THAT.
>> I SAID IF THE BILL WAS A
COMMISSION TO ESTABLISH TO STUDY
IT, WOULD HE SIGN IT?
>> IT WOULD HAVE TO GET THROUGH
THE HOUSE AND THE SENATE.
SO I CAN'T ANSWER YOU QUESTION.
IT'S A HYPOTHETICAL, REVEREND.
>> AND I'M ASKING YOU WOULD HE
SIGN IT AND SUPPORT IT?
>> I CAN'T ANSWER.
THE LAST SEGMENT YOU WERE IN,
YOU SAID THAT BLACK UNEMPLOYMENT
WAS LOWER THAN IT'S EVER BEEN
AND IT WAS GOING DOWN, BUT IT'S
STILL ALMOST DOUBLE THAT TO
WHITE.
WHAT IS THE PRESIDENT'S PLAN TO
DIRECTLY DEAL WITH THE
DISPROPORTIONATE AMOUNT OF
BLACKS TO WHITES?
>> ONE OF THE POLICIES A LOT OF
PEOPLE SUPPORT THE PRESIDENT IS
FIGHTING BACK AGAINST ILLEGAL
IMMIGRATION.
YOU AND I BOTH KNOW THAT IMPACTS
THE COMMUNITY WITH REGARDS TO I
DON'T SAY AND WAGES.
>> YOU'RE SAYING IMMIGRATION --
>> ILLEGAL IMMIGRANTS ARE NOT
MOVING IN TO GATED COMMUNITIES
OR IN THE POLITICIANS'
NEIGHBORS.
>> YOU'RE ARGUING THAT ILLEGAL
IMMIGRATION IS THE REASON THAT
BLACKS ARE ALMOST DOUBLY
UNEMPLOYED TO WHITES IN THIS
COUNTRY?
>> NO, YOU ASKED ME WHAT WAS A
CONTRIBUTOR.
>> I ASKED YOU WHAT HIS PLAN WAS
TO ADDRESS THE FACT THAT EVEN IN
A GOOD ECONOMY, BLACKS ARE
DOUBLY UNEMPLOYED TO WHITES.
THAT'S WHAT I ASKED YOU.
>> THE PROBLEM IS IT'S NOT GOOD
ENOUGH THAT IT'S GONE
DRASTICALLY LOW FOR YOU.
SO LET ME SAY ONCE AGAIN --
>> DAVID, LET ME GO TO YOU.
BECAUSE WHAT I'M SAYING IS THAT
EVEN IN GOOD TIMES -- I GAVE YOU
TWO OPPORTUNITIES.
>> THESE ARE GREAT TIMES.
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN DISCUSSED THE
INFUSION THAT THIS PRESIDENT HAS
HAD AN INFUSION OF CAPITAL.
>> THE REALITY IS PART OF HIS
BASE IS ATTRACTED TO DONALD
TRUMP BECAUSE HE'S A RACIST.
SO THERE'S NOT GOING TO BE ANY
PLAN.
ON THE DEMOCRATIC SIDE, THE GOOD
NEWS IS, AS JULIAN CASTRO WAS
JUST TALKING ABOUT ON THIS SHOW,
WE'RE GOING TO SEE A
GROUNDBREAKING DEMOCRATIC
PRIMARY WHERE THESE ISSUES ARE
RAISED, STRUCTURAL RACISM, THE
INCOME DISPARITY THAT YOU JUST
TALKED ABOUT.
I THINK THAT'S GOING TO BE A
HEALTHY DEBATE FOR THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
I THINK CANDIDATES ARE GOING TO
STAKE OUT DIFFERENT POSITIONS ON
THAT, BUT I THINK EVERYBODY WILL
COME AROUND TO THE VIEW.
AS A CONSERVATIVE COLUMNIST IN
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" SAID JUST
ADDRESSING THE ISSUE WILL START
TO HEAL THE COUNTRY.
>> 68% OF AMERICANS OPPOSITE
PAYING BLACK AMERICANS WHO ARE
DESCENDANTS OF SLAVES, BUT WHEN
WE LOOK BY RACE, MOST WHITE
AMERICANS OPPOSITE IT AND 60% OF
BLACK AMERICANS ARE FOR IT.
BUT LOOK AT THE DIVISION BY
PARTY.
WHILE 55% OF DEMOCRATS OPPOSITE
REPARATIONS, THE NUMBER IS MUCH
HIGHER IF YOU ASK REPUBLICANS.
86% AGAINST IT.
SO THERE IS THIS REAL DIFFERENCE
IN TERMS OF WHERE WE LOOK AT
REPARATIONS.
AND THE QUESTION OF RACE IS
DEFINITELY GOING TO BE IN THIS
CAMPAIGN.
LET ME ASK YOU THIS, KATRINA.
HISTORICALLY, REPUBLICANS AND
DEMOCRATS HAVE HAD MAJOR FIGURES
OF THE BLACK COMMUNITY IN THE
WEST WING AS PART OF THEIR
SENIOR STAFF AND ADMINISTRATION.
WHO ARE THE BLACKS IN THE WEST
WING UNDER PRESIDENT TRUMP?
>> YOU MEAN THOSE WHO ACTUALLY
TOOK THE JOB OR THOSE WHO'VE
BEEN OFFERED?
BECAUSE THOSE ARE ENTIRELY
DIFFERENT QUESTIONS.
>> THAT WORK IN THE WEST WING,
LET ME -- NO, I DIDN'T ASK YOU
OFFER.
I ASKED YOU -- WAIT A MINUTE.
LET ME ASK THE QUESTION.
I CAN UNDERSTAND WHY YOU'RE
NERVOUS.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO PARTICIPATE
IF YOU'RE GOING TO CONTINUE TO
PAINT THIS PRESIDENT AS RACIST.
>> CONNED LEE ZA RICE WITH BUSH,
COLIN POWELL WITH BUSH SR., IS
IT NOT A STRIKING CONTRAST, YET
THEY WANT TO APPEAL FOR BLACK
VOTES.
I ASKED YOU TO NAME THEM --
>> BECAUSE I'M NOT GOING TO
PARTICIPATE IN THE ATTEMPT TO
MAKE THIS ALL ABOUT RACE.
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
HOW MANY BLACK PEOPLE WERE IN
ABRAHAM LINCOLN'S WEST WING?
>> FIRST OF ALL, YOU'VE GOT TO
GO BACK TO ABE LINCOLN, YOU
REALLY NEED TO -- GEORGE BUSH.
>> IS ABRAHAM LINCOLN A RACIST
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T HAVE A BLACK
PERSON IN THE WHITE HOUSE?
THE THIS IS INSANE.
THIS IS AN INSANE DISCUSSION.
>> YOU CAN'T NAME A BLACK IN THE
WEST WING BECAUSE WE CAN'T FIND
ONE, KATRINA.
I PITY YOU.
I'D SYMPATHIZE WITH YOU, COME
ON.
IT'S UNTHINKABLE IN THE 21st
CENTURY THAT EVEN A SPOKESPERSON
FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP CAN'T NAME A
BLACK IN THE WEST WING.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AND YOU CONTRAST THAT WITH THE
RANGE OF DIVERSITY OF OUR
CANDIDATES ON OUR SIDE OF THE
PRESIDENTIAL PRIMARY THIS TIME,
THE RECORD NUMBER OF DIVERSE
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS ELECTED ON
THE DEMOCRATIC SIDE THIS LAST
TIME.
IT'S SUCH A STARK CONTRAST AND
IT'S AN EMBARRASSMENT THAT YOU
CAN'T COME UP WITH ONE NAME.
>> IT'S EXACTLY NOT AN
EMBARRASSMENT.
THIS GOES TO SHOW YOU HOW
RIDICULOUSLY PATHOLOGICAL
IDENTICAL POLITICS IS IN THIS
COUNTRY WHEN YOU HAVE SOMEBODY
LIKE WILL SMITH, WHO IS NOT EVEN
CONSIDERED BLACK ENOUGH TO
PORTRAY A BLACK MAN IN
HOLLYWOOD.
>> KATRINA, YOU BROUGHT UP, YOU,
EARLIER IN THE SHOW, HOW BLACK
UNEMPLOYMENT WAS SO LOW.
THAT WASN'T IDENTICAL POLITICS.
>> YES.
>> BUT WHEN I ASKED YOU ABOUT A
BLACK IN THE WEST WING, IT'S
IDENTICAL POLITICS.
AND YOU WONDER WHY THERE'S A
PROBLEM WITH BLACK VOTERS?
IF YOU WANT TO IDENTITY BLACK
UNEMPLOYMENT NUMBERS BUT CAN'T
IDENTITY A PROGRAM TO MAKE THEM
EQUAL TO THE REGULAR
UNEMPLOYMENT NUMBERS, THAT'S NOT
IDENTITY POLITICS.
>> BUT YOU WON'T LET ME SPEAK TO
TALK ABOUT THOSE PROGRAMS, LIKE
THE MONEY THAT'S GOING TO
MINORITY BUSINESSES AND MONEY
THAT'S GOING TO USE.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ABOUT THE
POLICIES.
>> I GAVE YOU EVERY OPPORTUNITY
AND I'LL GIVE YOU SOME MORE.
MAYBE YOU'LL FIND SOMEBODY IN
THE WEST WING BEFORE WE HAVE YOU
COMMON.
THANK YOU, KATRINA PIERSON, AND
THANK YOU, DAVID BROCK.
>>> COMING UP, HIP HOP ARTISTS
ARE GOING TO THE SUPREME COURT.
I'LL EXPLAIN NEXT.
(ding)
Hey, who are you?
Oh, hey Jeff, I'm a car thief...
What?!
I'm here to
steal your car because,
well, that's my job.
What?
What??
WHAT?!
(laughing)
What??
WHAT?!
What?!
[crash]
WHAT?!
Haha, it happens.
And if you've got
cut-rate car insurance,
paying for this could
feel like getting robbed twice.
So get Allstate...
and be better protected
from Mayhem...
like me.
♪
>>> NOW TIME FOR SOME HIP HOP.
SINCE ITS INCEPTION, RAP MUSIC
HAS BEEN JUDGED BOTH FAIRLY AND
UNFAIRLY ON ITS PROVOCATIVE
LYRICS AND OCCASIONAL BLAMED FOR
INCITING VIOLENCE.
THAT DEBATE WAS ELEVATED TO THE
HIGHEST COURT IN THE LAND THIS
WEEK WHEN A COALITION OF HIP HOP
ARTISTS FILED A LEGAL BRIEF WITH
THE UNITED STATES SUPREME COURT
ON BEHALF OF PITTSBURGH RAPPER
JAMAL KNOX, STAGE NAME MAYHEM
MILE.
IN
IN PRISON FOR LYRICS THREATENING
TWO POLICE OFFICERS IN A 2012
SONG.
ALLIES ARE CONTENDING THAT HIS
LYRICS WHILE PROVOCATIVE, FALL
WITHIN THE SCOPE OF PROTECTED
SPEECH BUT ARE BEING SUBJECTED
TO A DOUBLE STANDARD THAT IS
UNIQUE TO HIP HOP.
JOINING ME NOW, JAMILLA LAMAL,
COLUMNIST AND STRATEGIST.
WHICH WHOLE QUESTION OF WHY THEY
HAVE GONE AFTER THIS PARTICULAR
ARTIST, THIS PARTICULAR RAPPER,
AND NOW MANY IN THE HIP HOP
COMMUNITY HAVE COME TOGETHER AND
HAVE FILED A BRIEF ON HIS
BEHALF, GIVE US THE BACKGROUND
AND THE CONTENTION HERE.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, THERE ARE
DIFFERENT STANDARDS FOR
DIFFERENT GROUPS OF PEOPLE IN
THIS COUNTRY, AS WE KNOW, AND
UNFORTUNATELY THIS YOUNG MAN HAS
NOT BEEN ABLE TO EXPRESS HIS
LEGAL -- TO EXERCISE HIS LEGAL
RIGHT, TO EXPRESS HIMSELF
CREATIVELY.
A LOT OF US TAKE ISSUE WITH THE
VIOLENCE THIS RAP MUSIC.
IT'S SOMETHING YOU HAVE SPOKEN
OUT ABOUT IN THE PAST, IT'S
SOMETHING I TAKE ISSUE WITH.
LEGALLY THE ARTISTS HAVE THE
RIGHT TO SAY THINGS WE FIND TO
BE ABHORRENT.
HIS RECORD THAT SPEAKS OF
VIOLENCE AGAINST POLICE
OFFICERS, WE NEED TO TAKE A LOOK
AT ENTERTAINMENT FROM OTHER
GENERAS OF MUSIC, AND SAY HEY,
THERE ARE DEPICTIONS OF RAPE
HERE, ACTS OF VIOLENCE THAT ARE
NOT BEING PORTRAYED BY YOUNG
AFRICAN-AMERICAN MEN.
WE NEED TO INVESTIGATE THOSE AND
TAKE THEM SERIOUSLY.
WHAT THIS COMES DOWN TO IS THAT
IF A YOUNG BLACK MAN RECORDS A
SONG SAYING HE'S GOING TO DO
SOMETHING VIOLENT TOWARDS A
POLICE OFFICER, THAT THAT'S TO
BE TAKEN AS A LEGITIMATE THREAT
WHEN THERE HAVE BEEN INSTANCES
OF POLICE OFFICERS MAKING JOKES
ON SOCIAL MEDIA, ON FACEBOOK, IN
PRIVATE GROUPS, ON E-MAILS
DESCRIBING VIOLENCE AGAINST
MEMBERS OF THE COMMUNITIES THAT
THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO PROTECT AND
SERVE, AND THOSE THREATS, MANY
OF WHICH HAVE BEEN ACTED UPON,
AREN'T PUNISHED.
>> WHAT WE'RE REALLY SAYING HERE
IS THE ISSUE OF DOUBLE STANDARD,
WHETHER WE AGREE WITH THE LYRICS
OR NOT, AS YOU SAID, SOME OF US
HAVE OPPOSED SOME LYRICS OR NOT,
THE DOUBLE STANDARD BECAUSE IT
SEEMS SOME ARE REACHING A LEVEL
OF CRIMINALITY AND OTHERS ARE
JUDGED AS FREE SPEECH AND YOU
CAN'T HAVE A DOUBLE STANDARD IF
YOU'RE HAVING -- PARTICULARLY IF
YOU'RE GOING TO DEAL IN THE
CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> NOW, THE ARTISTS THAT ARE
SUPPORTING HIM, THE BASIS OF
THEIR BRIEF TO THE SUPREME COURT
IS THAT FREE SPEECH.
IF YOU DEEMED OTHER GENERAS OF
MUSIC THAT ALSO PROMOTES
VIOLENCE AND OTHER THINGS IS
FREE SPEECH, HOW IS THIS
DIFFERENT?
IS THAT THE BASIS?
AM I CORRECT ON THAT?
IS THAT THE BASIS OF THEIR
BRIEF?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THAT IS THE BASIS OF THIS
ARGUMENT.
TO SAY THAT WE'RE GOING TO TAKE
THE HYPERBOLIC LANGUAGE, WOULD
MEAN WE NEED TO APPLY THAT
STANDARD TO ALL MUSIC AND THAT'S
SIMPLY NOT WHAT WE DO.
I THOUGHT IT WAS INTERESTING
WHEN SUPREME COURT JUSTICE JOHN
ROBERTS MADE HIS ORIGINAL
STATEMENTS ABOUT THIS THAT HE
CHOSE TO CITE LYRICS BY THE
RAPPER EMINEM AND THAT'S NOT
LIKELY SOMEBODY WHO'S LIKELY TO
HAVE BEEN SUBJECTED TO
PUNISHMENT FOR THE THINGS HE
SAID UNDER THESE GROUNDS EVEN
THOUGH HIS MUSIC IS CHALK FULL
OF REFERENCE TO VIOLENCE AGAINST
HIS MOTHER, HIS FORMER PARTNER
BUT THIS LITTLE KNOWN ARTIST WHO
RECORDS A SONG USING LANGUAGE
THAT HAS BEEN USED IN HIP HOP
SINCE, YOU KNOW, NOT QUITE AT
ITS INCEPTION BUT SINCE ITS VERY
EARLY DAYS IS BEING TREATED AS
SUCH IS JUST ABSOLUTELY UNFAIR,
AND YOU KNOW, TO SUGGEST THAT
THIS IS ANYTHING BUT RACISM JUST
FEELS WRONG.
IT'S ONE OF THOSE THINGS THAT WE
CAN'T PROVE, RIGHT, WE KNOW IN
OUR GUT.
WE UNDERSTAND THAT YOU'RE
TREATING THIS YOUNG BLACK MAN,
YOU'RE TREATING THIS GENERA OF
ART THAT IS CREATED LARGELY BY
YOUNG BLACK MEN DIFFERENTLY THAN
WE TREAT OTHER ART FORMS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TELL US YOU'RE
DOING THIS BECAUSE THESE ARE
YOUNG BLACK MEN BUT WE
UNDERSTAND IT AND RECOGNIZE IT
KNOW IT.
>> THANK YOU, JAMELEAH.
UP NEXT, MY FINAL THOUGHTS.
STAY WITH US.
♪ ♪ ♪
Since my DVT blood clot
I was thinking...
could there be another
around the corner?
Or could it turn out
differently?
I wanted to help
protect myself.
My doctor
recommended ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS is proven to
treat and help prevent
another DVT
or PE blood clot...
Almost 98 percent of
patients on ELIQUIS
didn't experience another.
...and ELIQUIS has significantly
less major bleeding
than the standard treatment.
ELIQUIS is FDA approved
and has both.
Don't stop ELIQUIS
unless your doctor tells you to.
ELIQUIS can cause serious
and in rare cases
fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
If you had a spinal injection
while on ELIQUIS
call your doctor right away
if you have tingling, numbness,
or muscle weakness.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily...
and it may take
longer than usual
for bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden signs of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor
about all planned medical
or dental procedures.
What's around the corner
could be surprising.
Ask your doctor
about ELIQUIS.
Let's be honest:
dealing with your
insurance can be frustrating.
But with Esurance,
just snap some pics
and you could get
back on the road fast!
Well, not that fast.
This editor made this
commercial fit in 15 seconds.
When insurance is simple,
it's surprisingly painless.
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM SAYS
YOU CAN'T MAKE A
400 HORSEPOWER SEDAN,
THAT'S ALSO
ENVIRONMENTALLY CONSCIOUS.
WE DON'T FOLLOW
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>> AND NOW FOR MY FINAL
THOUGHTS.
ON THURSDAY, A JURY FOUND PALM
BEACH GARDENS, FLORIDA POLICE
OFFICER NEWMAN ROGER, GUILTY FOR
THE FATAL SHOOTING OF
31-YEAR-OLD CORY JONES WHO WAS
WAITING FOR ROADSIDE ASSISTANCE
ON THE NIGHT OF OCTOBER 18th,
2015.
WHEN ROGER IN PLAIN CLOTHES AND
DRIVING AN UNMARKED CAR STOPPED
TO INVESTIGATE AND ULTIMATELY
SHOT JONES, CONTENDING THAT HE
WAS ARMED WITH A GUN.
JONES WAS INDEED ARMED, LEGALLY,
AND ACCORDING TO PROSECUTORS
AFRAID FOR HIS LIFE WHEN HE WAS
SHOT THREE TIMES BY ROGER WHO
ACCORDING TO AUDIO FROM THE
SCENE NEVER IDENTIFIED HIMSELF
AS A COP.
I WAS ONE OF THOSE THAT PREACHED
AT CORY JONES' FUNERAL IN
NOVEMBER OF 2015.
AND ROGER WHO LATER LEFT THE
FORCE USED AS HIS DEFENSE, STAND
YOUR GROUND.
THE JURY CONVICTED HIM.
WHICH MEANS THAT AS WE LOOKED
LAST WEEK AT THE LACK OF
PROSECUTION IN SACRAMENTO AROUND
STEPHAN CLARK, AND AROUND
TERRANCE CRUTCHER IN TULSA,
OKLAHOMA, THERE ARE SOME
INJURIES THAT DO GET A CASE AND
DO SAY A POLICEMAN IS WRONG.
ALL POLICEMEN ARE NOT WRONG BUT
ALL OF THEM ARE NOT RIGHT.
WE MUST CORRECT A SYSTEM THAT
SAYS THAT WE WILL DISTINGUISH
CRIME WHETHER THE ACCUSED HAS ON
A BLUE UNIFORM OR BLUE JEANS,
TH