er brushing.
Oral-B just cleans better.
Even my hygienist said
going electric could lead to way
cleaner teeth.
And unlike Sonicare,
Even my hygienist said
Oral-B is the first electric
toothbrush brand
accepted by the ADA.
Oral-B.
Brush like a pro.
I have a vision
correction number,
But I'm more than a number.
When I'm not sharing ideas
with my colleagues
I'm defending my kingdom.
My Essilor lenses offer more
than vision correction
with three innovative
technologies
For my ultimate in vision
Clarity
And Protection
Together in a single lens:
The Essilor Ultimate
Lens Package.
So, I can do more
of what I love!
Buy two pairs of
Essilor's best lenses
and get a $100 back instantly.
See more. Do more. Essilor
>>> THAT'S OUR SHOW FOR TODAY.
SEE YOU TOMORROW ON "AM JOY."
THROWING ET OVER TO ALEX WHIT.
>> IF THEY CAN UNDERSTAND.
>> THEY CAN'T HAND TELL BETWEEN
SHOW.
>> SEND US THE SHOW.
IT WILL BE A SHOW ONE DAY.
THANK YOU, SEE YOU TOMORROW.
A VERY GOOD DAY FROM ALL OF YOU
IN NEW YORK.
WELCOME TO WEEKENDS WITH ALEX
WITT.
MICHAEL COHEN, WHAT HE BROUGHT
THIS WEEK?
A MEMBER OF THE INTEL HOUSE WILL
TALK TO ME TO TELL ME WHY THE
NEW DOCUMENTS MATTER SO MUCH.
>>> WHAT DOES THE DEPARTURE OF
THE SIXTH DIRECTO MEAN GOING
FORWARD?
AND THE PRESIDENT PAYING
RESPECTS TO AN ALABAMA HOME THAT
WAS HIT SO HARD.
WHY WAS HE SEENING BIBLES WHEN
THERE?
>>> HAPPENING NOW, THREE MAJOR
STORIES.
GROWING FALLOUT OVER THE
SENTENCING OF FORMER CAMPAIGN
PAUL MANAFORT.
DEMOCRATS FACING A GROWING
BACKLASH OVER CONGRESSWOMAN
ILHAN OMAR AND 2020 HOPEFULS ARE
MAKING THEIR CASE ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
AFTER TOURING THE DAMAGE IN
ALABAMA, THE PRESIDENT SIGNED
BIBLES.
HIS TEAM SED SAYS PEOPLE IN A
BAPTIST CHURCH ASKED HIM FOR HIS
AUTOGRAPH.
BEFORE LEAVING, THE PRESIDENT
SIGNED SIDED WITH MANAFORT.
MANY BELIEVE IT WAS A LENIENT
SENTENCE FOR MULTI-MILLION
DOLLAR CRIMES.
>> I FEEL BADLY FOR PAUL
MANAFORT.
THE JUDGE SAID THERE WAS NO
COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA.
I DON'T EVEN DISCUSS IT.
THE ONLY ONE DISCUSSING IT IS
YOU.
I HAVEN'T DISCUSSED IT.
>> WELL, TO BE TOTALLY CLEAR.
JUDGE TS ELLIOT DID NOT S
THERE WAS NO COLLUSION, BUT
MANAFORT WAS NOT BEING SENTENCED
FOR CRIMES RELATED TO COLLUSION.
THERE IS DISTINCTION THERE.
>>> ALSO DEVELOPING THIS HOUR,
ALMOST A WEEK OF HER
ANTI-SEMITIC COMMENTS, DEMOCRAT
OMAR FIND HERSELF AT THE OPEN OF
DISCUSSION AFTER SAYING THIS
ABOUT PRESIDENT OBAMA.
WE CAN'T ONLY BE UPSET WITH
TRUMP.
HIS POLICIES ARE BAD BUT MANY OF
THE PEOPLE WHO CAME BEFORE HIM
ALSO HAD REALLY BAD POLICIES.
THEY JUST WERE MORE POLISHED
THAN HE WAS.
I WOULD TALK ABOUT THE FAMILY
SEPARATION OR CAGEING OF KIDS
AND PEOPLE WOULD POINT OUT THAT
THIS WAS TRUMP.
I MEAN, THIS WAS OBAMA.
I WOULD SAY SOMETHING ABOUT THE
DRONING OF COUNTRIES AROUND THE
WORLD AND PEOPLE WOULD SAY IT
WAS A OBAMA.
>> WELL, EARLIER, I SPOKE WELL
NOR HOLMES NORTON, THE
DEMOCRATIC CONGRESSWOMAN
REPRESENTING DVENLTH LISTEN TO
HER ACTION OF OMAR'S CRITICISM
OF PRESIDENT OBAMA.
>> I'M ALMOST RELIEVED.
BECAUSE IT LOOKS LIKE HE IS SHE
IS AN EQUAL OPPORTUNITY CRITIC.
I TELL YOU, I THINK THE
PRODUCTION I PRODUCT OF SOCIAL
MEDIA, WHEN PEOPLE HEAR HER NO
THEY ARE PROBABLY WRITING HER
OFF.
NO EXPERIENCE, HOW ARE YOU TO
UNDERSTAND HOW ARE YOU TO BEHAVE
AS A MEMBER OF CONGRESS.
IN TERMS OF HER SPEAKING HER
MIND.
THAT'S WHAT FREE SPEECH IS ALL
ABOUT.
>> DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES BACK
OUT ON THE CAMPAIGN TRAIL, IN
FACT, DEMOCRAT BERNIE SANDERS IS
SPEAKING TO PEOPLE IN IOWA.
WE WILL BRING YOU HIS FRIENDS
AND LATER THIS HOUR, WE WILL
BRING YOU THE STRATEGIST.
THE QUESTION IS WHY HE LEFT AND
WHAT HE THINKS ABOUT SANDER,'
NEW RUN FOR PRESIDENT.
MEANWHILE, PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
RAILING AGAINST HIS FORMER
ATTORNEY MICHAEL COHEN CALLING
HIM A LIAR FOR CLAIMING UNDER
OATH HE NEVER ASKED FOR A
PARDON.
KELLY O'DONNELL IS JOINING US
FROM WEST PALM BEACH, FLORIDA,
RIGHT HERE WHERE THE PRESIDENT
IS SPENDING HIS WEEKEND.
WHAT IS HAPPENING ON THIS FRONT?
>> Reporter: WELL, ANNA, ON A
WINDY SATURDAY HERE IN WEST PALM
BEACH, LET ME TELL YOU THE
PRESIDENT HAS BEEN HAMMERING
AWAY AT MICHAEL CON.
TODAY HE'S AT HIS GOLF COURSE,
WHERE PRESUMABLY HE IS GETTING
SOME OF THAT ENERGY OUT DRIVING
ON THE LINKS, B BEFORE HE LEFT
THE WHITE HOUSE, HE WAS VERY
SHARP IN HIS CRITICISM OF COHEN
AND FOR AS LONG AS MICHAEL COHEN
IS HEADING TO PRISON AND
AVAILABLE TO CONGRESS AND
OTHERS, THE PRESIDENT MAY SEE
HIM AS AN OPPORTUNITY TARGET TO
GO AFTER HIM, TRYING TO EXPLOIT
A PERCEIVED DISCREPANCY IN
COHEN'S OWN COMMENTS ABOUT A
REQUEST FOR A PARDON.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS IMPRESSED BY
THIS FROM REPORTERS AS HE WAS
HEADEDAWAY FROM THE WHITE HOUSE
ON FRIDAY.
HERE'S HOW HE LAID OUT ABOUT
HEN AND THE DISPARITY ON
COHEN'S POSITION ON WHETHER OR
NOT HE EVER WANTED A PARDON.
>> I KNOW THAT IN WATCHING AND
SEEING YOU FOLKS AT NIGHT THAT
MICHAEL COHEN LIED ABOUT THE
PARDON.
IT WAS A STONE COLD LIE.
HE LIED ABOUT A LOT OF THINGS.
WHEN HE LIED ABOUT THE PARDON.
THAT WAS A LIE.
HE KNEW ABOUT PARDONS.
HIS LAWYER, SAID THEY WENT TO MY
LAWYER AND ASKED FOR PARDONS.
I CAN GO A STEP ABOVE THAT.
I WON'T GO INTO IT NOW.
>> Reporter: WELL, WHEN THE
PRESIDENT WAS ON THE PLANE, HE
TALKED ABOUT MICHAEL COHEN SAY
HE HAD PERSONALLY ASKED THE
PRESIDENT FOR A PARDON WHEN THEY
WERE STILL ON SPEAKING TERMS.
>> THAT IS DIFFERENT WHAT HIS
LAWYERS SAY.
THEY SAY THEY HAD IM INQUIRED
ABOUT THE POSSIBILITY OF A
PARDON WHEN THEY WERE OPERATING
UNDER WHAT IS KNOWN AS A JOINT
DEFENSE AGREEMENT WHEN THERE ARE
SORT OF ALLIES FACING
PROSECUTIONS AND DOCUMENT AND
INFORMATION.
THEY WERE WORKING TOGETHER AT
THAT TIME.
UNTIL MICHAEL COHEN WAS INDICTED
AND LATER COOPERATED AND THAT
AGREEMENT CLEANED UP.
COHEN FIRED BACK WITH HIS OWN
TWEET CALLING THAT ALL LIES,
ENCOURAGING THE PRESIDENT TO USE
WHAT WAS THE INTERNATIONAL
WOMEN'S DAY TO MAKE HIS OWN
APOLOGY, SAID COHEN, TWO WOMEN
HE HAD SOME RELATIONSHIP WITH IN
TERMS OF A CANDIDATE, TWO WOMEN
WHO RECEIVED PAYMENTS IN THE
LARGE SCHEME OF THINGS TO TRY TO
CONCEAL THOSE PERSONAL
RELATIONSHIPS THEY HAD WITH THE
PRT THAT HE DENIES, SO
MICHAEL COHEN AND THE PRESIDENT
ENTANGLED AGAIN ON TWITTER AND
IN THEIR COMMENTS PUBLICLY.
>> OH, YEAH, IT IS WINDY DOWN
THERE.
WE WILL SEE YOU NEXT HOUR.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
JOINING ME A DEMOCRAT FROM THE
HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE.
I'M GOING TO GET TO WHAT
HAPPENED BEHIND CLOSED DOORS IN
FRONT OF YOUR COMMITTEE
REGARDING MICHAEL COHEN LATER.
I DO WANT TO START WITH THE
COMMENTS, NEW ONES BY YOUR
CONGRESSMAN ILHAN OMAR.
SHE COMPLAINS ABOUT TRUMP,
SAYING WE CAN'T BE ONLY UPSET
ABOUT TRUMP.
HIS POLICIES ARE BAD.
BUT MANY OF THE PEOPLE WHO CAME
BEFORE HIM ALSO HAD PROBLEMS.
DOES IT HELP, SIR, FOR
DEMOCRATS, THE DEMOCRATS TO
REVISIT THE OBAMA LEGACY FOR
2020?
>> SO LOOK, ALEX, I DON'T KNOW
ANY DEMOCRAT WHO WOULDN'T SAY ON
OCCASION THEY DISAGREED WITH
PRESIDENT OBAMA'S POLICIES.
I DON'T KNOW A SINGLE DEMOCRAT
THAT WOULDN'T SWAP OUT PRESIDENT
OBAMA FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP IN A
NEW YORK SECOND.
THE FACT IS AN OVERWHELMING
NUMBER OF DEMOCRATS STRONGLY
SUPPORT PRESIDENT OBAMA IN MOST
OF HIS POLICIES, OH LORD, WOULD
I LOVE TO HAVE HIM BACK AGAIN.
>> I THINK A FEW PEOPLE FEEL
THAT WAY.
WITH REGARD TO THE
CONGRESSWOMAN, IS IT RUSHING THE
STATE TO SPEAK LIKE THAT?
>> WELL, I THINK SHE IS IN A
DIFFERENT FISH BOWL THAN SHE HAS
SAID BEFORE.
ANY UTTERANCE AT ANY TIME WILL
BE AMPLIFIED.
IF SHE DOESN'T DO IT, HERSELF.
IT WILL BE RESPONDED TO IN A WAY
THAT SHE HAS EVER SEEN BEFORE.
LET'S HOPE THERE ARE GROWTH AND
LEARNING PAINS GOING ON HERE.
>> SO YOU AND YOUR COLLEAGUES
PASSED A COMPREHENSIVE AND
CORRUPTIBLE ANTI-LEGISLATION.
IT WAS BRAIS PLACED ON
CONDEMNING ALL FORMS OF HATE AS
THEY ARE LINGERING OVER THE
ANTI-SEMITIC COMMENTS.
WHY DID HER COMMENTS GET
ATTENTION ON BOT SIDES OF THE
AISLE?
DO YOU THINK IT REFLECTS A
GENERATIONAL DIVIDE OR
REPUBLICANS ARE TRYING TO MAKE
IT LOOK THAT WAY?
>> SO I THOUGHT THE THING ABOUT
THE ANTI-HATE PATH.
FIRST OF WHICH IS THAT THERE ARE
23 REPUBLICANS WHO VOTED FOR
HATE OR AGAINST OPPOSITION TO
HATE.
I SIMPLY FAIL TO UNDERSTAND
THAT.
ONE WENT SO FAR AS TO SAY
BECAUSE IT DIDN'T HAVE AN
ANTI-WHITE DISCRIMINATION CLAUSE
IN IT HE COULDN'T SUPPORT IT.
ONE THING IN SPITE OF ALL THE
MEDIA ATTENTION GIVEN TO THAT
PARTICULAR RESOLUTION, WHICH
PASSED OVERWHELMINGLY, WE ALSO
TOOK UP THE SWEEPING ETHICS
REFORM MEASURE IN A GENERATION.
SO WE DID NOT ALLOW ALL THAT
ATTENTION ON THURSDAY TO
DISTRACT US AS WE WERE DRAINING
THE SWAMP AND MAKING SURE PEOPLE
CAN HAVE CONFIDENCE IN THE
ELECTORAL SYSTEM.
>> YEAH.
SUPER IMPORTANT.
NOW WE'LL GET NO WHAT HAPPENED
WITH LAWYER MICHAEL COHEN
TESTIFYING AGAIN BEHIND CLOSED
DOORGS TO YOUR COMMITTEE.
WE SAW HIM WHEEL IN THESE
DOCUMENTS.
SOURCES SAY HE SUPPORTS OPEN
TESTIMONY WEDNESDAY OF LAST
WEEK.
SO WHAT YOU CAN TELL US IN THOSE
DOCUMENTS, DID YOU FIND EVIDENCE
THAT SUPPORTS ANY OF THE ONGOING
INVESTIGATIONS, THAT WOULD
INCLUDE OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
>> I THINK I WOULD ASSUME THE
PHRASE, YOU ARE ASSUMINGACTS
THAT CONTAIN DOCUMENTS.
>> YOU ARE NOT GOING TO ANSWER
IT, ARE YOU?
>> NO WE HAVE DONE IT TOO MANY
TIMES.
I WILL TELL YOU THIS, I
GENUINELY BELIEVE I HAVE LEARNED
AS MUCH IF NOT MORE IN THE TWO
DAYS THE OF INTERVIEWING MICHAEL
COHEN THIS WEEK AND LAST WEEK
THAN I DID IN TWO YEARS UNDER
THE INVESTIGATION UNDER THE
REPUBLICAN MAJORITY.
IT WAS A SUBSTANTIVE EXCHANGE.
HE WAS FULLY COOPERATIVE.
I THINK IT MATERIALLY
CONTRIBUTED TO OUR INVESTIGATORY
EFFORTS.
WE WILL, OF COURSE, AS IN ALL
GOODS INVESTIGATIONS INSIST ON
HAVING CORROBORATING EVERYDAY.
>> WHEN YOU SAY YOU LEARNED SO
MUCH IN THESE TWO EPISODES WITH
HIM, THAT WAS ALL THE BEHIND
CLOSED DOORS.
YOU ARE NOT INCLUDING WHAT WE
HAVE ALL HEARD ON WEDNESDAY OF
LAST WEEK?
>> NO I THINK THERE IS A
DIFFERENT PURPOSE AND A DIFFER
TONE.
THE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE WHICH
DID A EXCELLENT JOB HAS A
DIFFERENT LANE.
AS YOU KNOW, OUR EFFORTS FOCUS
ON COUNTERINTELLIGENCE ALSO
NOTABLY WITH ALL DUE RESPECT TO
THE PROFESSION YOU WERE IN AND I
WAS IN FOR TEN YEARS.
THERE IS A DIFFERENT TENOR THAT
OCCURS WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE
CAMERAS IN THE ROOM.
IT'S MORE SERIOUS, I THINK.
>> YOU KNOW IF I DIDN'T LIKE YOU
SO MUCH.
LET'S LISTEN WHAT COHEN TOLD THE
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE SPECIFICALLY
WITH REGARD TO THE PRESIDENTIAL
PARDON.
HERE'S THAT.
>> I HAVE NEVER ASKED FOR, NOR
WOULD I ACCEPT A PARDON FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> SO WHEN HE TESTIFIED BEFORE
YOUR COMMITTEE THE I GET YOU TO
ANSWER WHETHER OR NOT THE ISSUE
OF A PRESIDENTIAL PARDON CAME
UP?
JUST THE ISSUE?
SO, ALEX, I THINK COMMON SENSE
WOULD SUGGEST ANYBODY TO A
LOGICAL CONCLUSION ON THAT
QUESTION.
LET ME GO BACK TO THE ISSUE OF
THE SENSITIVITY ABOUT THE
ABSENCE OF CAMERAS AND TO REMIND
YOU THAT THE TRANSVICTIMS OF
THESE TWO INTERVIEW SESSIONS
WILL BE RELEASED IN THE NOT TOO
DISTANT FUTURE.
IT HASN'T BEEN DETERMINED THAT
DATE.
YOU CORNER HAVE THAT LONG TO
WAIT BEFORE YOU CAN SEE EVERY
WORD ASKED AND EVERY WORD
ANSWERED.
>> OKAY.
WHAT ABOUT REPORTING THAT
MICHAEL COHEN'S LAWYERS FIRST
FLOATED THE IDEA OF A PARDON
WITH THE PRESIDENT'S LEGAL TEAM.
CAN I ASK YOU IF YOU HAVE THE
EVIDENCE TO DETERMINE WHETHER OR
NOTE LIE TO CONGRESS A SECOND
TIME?
>> YOU CAN ASK.
>> OH, PLEASE.
SO HOW ABOUT THIS, THE WHOLE
EPISODE ALTOGETHER HAS THIS
UNDERMINED HIS CREDIBILITY FOR
YOU OR DO YOU FIND HIS TESTIMONY
CREDIBLE?
>> SO HE WAS INCREDIBLY
COOPERATIVE.
AS WE ALL WELL KNOW, AS HAS BEEN
REPRESENTED IN OPEN SOURCES, HE
BROUGHT RECEIPTS.
HE DID BRING DOCUMENTS.
I'M NOT GETTING INTO EXACTLY
WHAT THEY WERE.
IT IS A QUESTION NOW OF PIECING
TOKE THE WHOLE CLOTH.
IT'S NOT APPROPRIATE OR PRUDENCE
OF STANDARD PRACTICES TO DRA ANY
HARD AND FAST PIECE OF TESTIMONY
OR ONE DOCUMENT.
ALL OF THESE HAVE TO BE PIECED
TOGETHER.
IT WILL INCLUDING GATHERING
INFORMATION FROM PEOPLE BEYOND
MICHAEL CON.
AS OF COURSE, YOU KNOW THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE HAS
ANNOUNCED WE WILL HAVE FELIX
SADER IN FOR AN OPEN SESSION I
BELIEVE LATER ON THIS MONTH.
THAT'S A PIECE AND PARCEL OF
THIS AS WELL.
>> IT IS, INDEED, AS TALKING
WITH YOU AND GETTING WHAT WE
CAN.
I DO APPRECIATE THE CANDOR YOU
ARE ABLE TO GIVE US.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> DIVIDE AND CONQUER, HOW
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS EMPLOYED
THAT STRATEGY IN HIS BATTLE FOR
RE-ELECTION.
>>>
.
>>> I THOUGHT YESTERDAY'S VOTE
BY THE HOUSE WAS DISGRACEFUL
BECAUSE IT'S BECOME THE
DEMOCRATS HAVE BECOME AN
ANTI-ISRAEL PARTY.
THEY'VE BECOME AN ANTI-JEWISH
PARTY.
>> HMM, THE PRESIDENT
CRITICIZING DEMOCRATS AFTER THEY
OVERWHELMINGLY PASSED A HOUSE
RESOLUTION CONDEMNING NOT JUST
ANTISEMITISM AND RACE ACROSS THE
BOARD.
JOINING ME NOW A NATIONAL
POLITICAL REPORTER FOR "THE
WASHINGTON POST" AND BRIAN
BENNETT, SENIOR CORRESPONDENT
FOR "TIME" MAGAZINE.
NICE TO SEE YOU, BRYANT I'LL
START WITH YOU FIRST.
DO YOU UNG THE DEMOCRATS OPENED
THEMSELVES UP TO CRITICISM BY
ALLOWING THIS RESOLUTION TO
PERCOLATING AS LONG AS IT DID
BEFORE PASSING IT?
>> THIS IS NOT WHAT THE
DEMOCRATS WANT TO BE TALKING
ABOUT.
IT PLAYS INTO TRUMPS PLAN ABOUT
WHO IS ALIVE WITH ISRAEL AND
NOT.
REP OMAR WITH HER COMMENTS HAVE
OPENED THIS UP FOR THE
DEMOCRATS.
THEY FELT THEY HAD TO DO
SOMETHING.
IT KEPT IT UP IN THE DEBATE FOR
SO LONG.
WHAT THEY WANT TO TALK ABOUT IS
WHAT THEY ARE DOING TO
COUNTERCORRUPTION.
THE MASSIVE INVESTIGATIONS INTO
TRUMP'S ALLEGED ACTIVITY THEY'VE
LAUNCHED AND THEY WANT TO TALK
ABOUT THE VOTING RIGHTS BILL
THEY'VE PASSED.
THEY DON'T WANT TO BE TALKING
ABOUT THIS DIVISIVE ISSUE.
>> I WILL GET TO REPRESENTATIVE
OMAR WITH YOU IN A MOMENT.
FELICIA, YOU SPECIFICALLY
REPORTEDTHON AND HOW IT CREATED
VISION IN THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY.
WHY DID IT DIVIDE DEMOCRATS?
>> IT'S INTERESTING.
LEADING UP TO THE ACTUAL VOTE ON
THURSDAY.
THIS DID TEAR DEMOCRATS APART.
YOU HAVE MEMBERS OF THE OLD
GUARD CALLING FOR THIS YOU HAD
SOME MEMBERS SAYING THIS SHOULD
BE DIRECTED TOWARDS
ANTI-SEMITISM AND CALLING FOR
THIS TO BE A NARROW RESOLUTION.
ON THE OTHER HAND YOU HAVE
MEMBERS OF THIS NEWLY EMBOLDENED
FRESHMAN CLASS SAYING I NOT
ABOUT THIS ONE SPECIFIC HATE.
WE WANT TO BROADEN IT OUT
AGAINST HATE AND ALL DIFFERENT
KIND OF GROUPS.
SO YOU SAW ON THURSDAY THE
MEASURE WAS ABOUT TO HIT THE
FLOOR AND GOT PULLED OFF AND
FINALLY DID COME DOWN FOR A
VOTE.
WHAT I THOUGHT WHAT WAS
INTERESTING IN THE FINAL TALLY,
THE FOCUS HAD BEEN ABOUT THE
DEBATE IN THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
ON THIS.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, EVERY
DEMOCRAT VOTED IN FAVOR.
YOU HAD 23 HOUSE REPUBLICANS
VOTING AGAINST IT.
NOW THEY ALL GAVE VARIOUS
REASONS, SOME HOUSE REPUBLICANS
SAID THEY THOUGHT IT WAS WATERED
DOWN.
SON SOME FAVORED A NARROW
ANTI-SEMITISM AND ANOTHER MO
BROOKS FROM ALABAMA SAYING THAT
HE THOUGHT THIS SHOULD HAVE BEEN
BROADER AND INCLUDING
DISCRIMINATION OF OTHER GROUPS
OF CHRISTIANS OR CAUCASIANS.
YOU HAD SEVERAL MEMBERS ON THE
FLOOR AS WELL SUCH AS DOUG
COLLINS FROM GEORGIA, BRINGING
UP THAT VERY POINT.
SO IT'S INTERESTING THIS DEBATE
HAS MANY DO WENT IN SOME
DIRECTION.
>> PERHAPS NOT WHAT WAS INTENDED
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
OKAY.
SO REPRESENTATIVE OMAR, YOU
KNOW, ONE OF THESE NEWLY
EMBOLDENED ONES, ONE FELICIA
IDENTIFIED THEM.
FEATURED IN AN INTERVIEW WITH
POLITICO MAGAZINE.
HER COMMENTS ABOUT PRESIDENT
OBAMA ARE GETTING SOME TRACTION.
LET'S TAKE A LISTEN TO SOME OF
WHAT SHE SAID.
>> WE CAN'T BE ONLY UPSET WITH
TRUMP.
HIS PALESS ARE BAD, BUT MANY OF
THE PEOPLE WHO CAME BEFORE HIM
ALSO HAD REALLY BAD POLICIES.
THEY WERE JUST MORE POLISHED
THAN HE WAS.
I WOULD TALK ABOUT THE FAMILY
SEPARATION OR CAGEING OF KIDS
AND PEOPLE WOULD POINT OUT THAT
THCHS TRUMP, I MEAN, THIS WAS
OBAMA.
I WOULD SAY SOMETHING ABOUT THE
DRONING OF COUNTRIES AROUND THE
WORLD AND PEOPLE WOULD SAY THAT
WAS OBAMA.
>> HOW DO YOU SEE THIS PLAYING
OUT, BRIAN?
SMR ONCE AGAIN, THIS PLAYS INTO
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S HANDS, HE HAS
BEEN CRITICAL OF OBAMA'S POLICY
ON THE RIGHT.
NOW YOU HAVE REPRESENTATIVE
OMAREK CO-ING VOICES OF THE LEFT
DURING OBAMA'S PRESIDENCY, WHO
FELT HE WAS GOVERNING WITH HALF
MEASURES AND NOT GOING FAR
ENOUGH OF BIG PICTURE POLICIES.
IT'S TRUE, I COVERED THE OBAMA
PRESIDENCY.
IT WASN'T UNTIL THE SECOND TERM
THAT HE DESIGNED THE DACA
PROGRAM AND RULED THAT OUT AFTER
MASSIVE PRESSURE FROM THE LEFT.
SO WE SHOULDN'T BE SURPRISED TO
HEAR THIS BUBBLING BACK UP
COMING FROM REPRESENTATIVE OMAR
AND OTHERS WHO HAVE COME IN FROM
INTO CONGRESS TRYING TO BRING
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY IN THEIR
VIEW TO BIGGER AND BOLDER IDEAS.
SHE IS TALKING ABOUT LEGITIMATE
DISAPPOINTMENT THAT SHE AND
OTHERS ON THE LEFT.
>> I WANT TO BEGIN WITH PAUL
MANAFORT AND BEGIN WITH YOU.
YOU WROTE ABOUT THIS.
IF HE WOULD HAVE NEVER JOINED
TRUMP'S CAMPAIGN, PAUL MANAFORT
WOULD BE LIKELY A FREE MAN
TODAY?
DO YOU THINK THAT WILL FACTOR
INTO HIS PARDONING ABOUT THAT?
>> WE HEARD ABOUT THE PRESIDENT
HAS CALLED HIM A GOOD MAN.
>> FEELS BAD FOR HIM.
>> YEAH.
HE FEELS BAD FOR HIM.
SO IT' ENTIRELY POSSIBLE THOUGH
HE DOESN'T HAVE A GREAT TRACK
RECORD IN THAT REGARD.
IT IS TRUE IF YOU THINK ABOUT
MANAFORT, IT'S ENTIRELY POSSIBLE
HE WOULD HAVE GOTTEN AWAY FROM
HIDING DOLLARS FROM TAX
AUTHORITIES IF HE HADN'T MET
TRUMP.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO THINK OF WHERE
WE ARE.
WE HAVE A SITTING PRESIDENT, HIS
CAMPAIGN MANAGER FOR THOSE TWO
CRITICAL MONTHS IS NOW GOING TO
JAIL FOR TAX FRAUD AND BANK
FRAUD.
NOW THAT DOESN'T SPEAK TO THE
NTL QUESTION OF THE MUELLER
PROBE.
BUT WHICH IS RUSSIAN
INVOLVEMENT.
BUT IT DOES SPEAK TO THE
PRESIDENT'S JUDGMENT IN HIRING
HIM, NOT LOOKING AT HIS PAST AND
THEN OF COURSE WE FOUND OUT
DURING THE PROCEEDINGS BECAUSE
OF A MISTAKE IN THE COURT FILING
THAT HE MET WITH CONTAIN TEEN
KILIMNIK, A RUSSIAN OPERATIVE
AND HAD ALLEGEDLY GIVEN HIM
CAMPAIGN POLLING DATA.
>> RIGHT.
>> SO THAT WASN'T A PART OF WHAT
HE WAS CONVICTED OF AND GOING TO
JALG NOW.
BUT THAT INFORMATION IS NOW OUT
THERE AND IT HURTS THE
PRESIDENT.
>> WE HAVE TO SAY THAT IS
SPECIFICALLY WHAT THE JUDGE
SAID.
AGAIN WHAT HE WAS SENTENCED FOR.
ENGLISH SHA, QUICKLY, HOW'D THIS
ALL -- FELISHA, WHERE IS THIS
HEADING?
>> SEVERAL CANDIDATES HAVE COME
OUT TO USE THE MANAFORT
SENTENCING TO MAKE THEIR CASE ON
THE NEED FOR CRIMINAL JUSTICE
REFORM.
I THINK THAT'S A DEBATE THAT'S
ENERGIZED A LOT OF VOTERS IE
DEMOCRATIC BASE RIGHT NOW.
BRIAN MENTIONED BEYOND THE
SENTENCE, ITSELF IS REALIZING
THIS IS ONE OF THE MANY LEGAL
WOES THE PRESIDENT IS EXPECTING.
WE IMAGINE THE MUELLER REPORT TO
COME OUT ONE DAY THIS WEEK.
>> THAT WILL ONLY BECOME A LEGAL
MARASS FOR HIM.
THE DEMOCRATS ARE INVESTIGATING
HIM AND GOING BEYOND THE
PRESIDENT, HIMSELF, TO EXAMINE
FOR INSTANCE THE ALLEGATIONS OF
MISCONDUCT IN GEORGIA WHEN IT
COMES TO ISSUES OF VOTER RIGHTS
THERE.
>> THERE'S A LITTLE STILL
PERCOLATING WE WILL HAVE TO TALK
ABOUT IN THE FUTURE.
THANKS, GUYS.
2020 TENSION BETWEEN SANDERS
CAMPAIGN STAFFERS AND CLINTON
CAMPAIGN OFFICIALS.
SO WHAT IS THE TRUTH?
A FORMER CAMPAIGN INSIDER WILL
JOIN US.
I Hear it in the Background and
she's Watching too, saying
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
♪
[FRIEND]
I've never seen thatefore.
♪
I have...
Since I'm a truck driver,
sometimes I'm gone
for, like,
three weeks at a time.
Even if I'm 3,000 miles away,
I'm connected with my boys.
Just pull on over,
see my son's game,
and I'm having a ball.
(VO)
There when it matters.
Buy the new Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e on us.
Gentle means everything.
So we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients.
Added
one-handed pumps.
And beat the top
safety standards.
JOHNSON'S®
Choose gentle.
Termites,
feasting on homes 24/7.
We're on the move.
Roger.
Hey Rick, all good?
Oh yeah, we're good.
We're good.
Termites never stop trying to
get in,
we never stop working to keep
them out.
Terminix.
Defenders of Home.
>>> THE NATURE OF OUR CAMPAIGN
IS NOT BELITTLING PEOPLE.
IT'S NOT OPPOSITION RESEARCH.
IMTS NOT ATTACKING OTHER PEOPLE.
IT'S A SERIOUS DISCUSSION ABOUT
THE IMPORTANT ISSUES FACING THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
IF WE DO NOT WHEN I WILL
STRONGLY SUPPORT THE DEMOCRATIC
NOMINEE AND HOPE AND BELIEVE
OTHERS FEEL EXACTLY THE SAME
WAY.
DONALD TRUMP MUST BE DEFEATED.
>> DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATE BERNIE SANDERS
SPEAKING A FEW MOMENTS AGO IN
DESMOINES, IOWA, JOINING ME A
FORMER SENIOR ADVISER.
WELCOME TO YOU.
WE WANT TO GET INTO THIS WITH
YOU.
WE HAVE THE "NEW YORK TIMES"
QUOTING YOU SAYING YOU HAVE
STRATEGIC DIFFERENCES WITH
SANDERS AND HIS WIFE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO MAKE YOU LEAVE?
>> AS WE SAID IN A STATEMENT
SET, WE FELT SANDERS HAD A
CREATIVE VISION FOR THE
CAMPAIGN.
WE FELT WE WEREN'T ON THE SAME
PAGE.
WE WANTED TO STEP AWAY SO HE CAN
PUT A TEAM AROUND HIM THAT
SHARED THE DIRECTION HE WANT
TODAY GO IN.
I WANT TO SAY THIS IS VERY
AMICABLE.
WE LEFT THE SANDERS' CAMPAIGN ON
A POSITIVE NOTE.
WE ARE PROUD OF THE WORK WE DID
FOR HIM IN 2016.
I'M STILL VERY APPRECIATIVE OF
HIM ALLOWING US TO BE A PART OF
THAT CAMPAIGN.
>> OKAY.
LET'S GET TO WHAT THERE HAS BEEN
A SLEW OF REPORTING ON, BOTH THE
PUBLIC AND PRIVATE FEUDING
BETWEEN THE CLINTON AND CAMPAIGN
STAFFERS.
DID YOU SEE ANY OF THAT SAND
WHAT IS IT ABOUT THE RIVALRY
THAT MAKES IT' HARD TO LET IT
GO?
BEFORE I HAVE YOU ANSWER THAT IT
STRUCK ME LISTENING TO BERNIE
SANDERS THERE, IF HE SAID I DO
NOT WIN, I WILL STRONGLY SUPPORT
THE DEMOCRATIC NOMINEE.
DO YOU THINK THE LEFTOVER
RESENTMENT IS THE FACT THAT HE
TOOK A LONG TIME TO GET AROUND
TO THAT LAST GO AROUND?
>> I DON'T AGREE.
I THINK HE CAMPAIGNED HARD FOR
HILLARY CLINTON IN THE LAST
CAMPAIGN.
>> DID HE DO IT AS SOON?
WAS IT PRETTY EVIDENT HE WAS NOT
GOING TO GET THE NOMINATION?
>> I THINK HE SAID HE WAS GOING
ULTIMATELY THROUGH THE PRIMARIES
AND ENDORSED HILLARY CLINTON NOT
TOO LONG AFTER THAT WE PUT 2016
IN THE REAR VIEW MIRROR.
WE FACED A THREAT AND DEMOCRATS
NEED TO CENTRALIZE AROUND ONE
FINAL IDEA WHICH IS WE FEED TO
GET RID OF DONALD TRUMP.
I THINK A LOT OF THIS ANIMOSITY
FROM 2016, WE NEED TO LEAVE IT
BEHIND.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE WILL AGREE
WITH YOU, GET RID OF DONALD
TRUMP.
IS THAT ENOUGH?
IS THAT ENOUGH FOR DEMOCRATS TO
RUN ON?
THEY'VE GOT TO HAVE THEIR OWN
PLATFORMS.
ARE THEY MORE LEFT OR MORE
PROGRESSIVE?
SPEAK TO ALL THAT.
>> I THINK ELIZABETH WARREN HAS
A SHARP POSITIVE MESSAGE THAT'S
RESONATEING.
COREY BOOKER HAS A WEIDENAARTIVE
HE IS TALKING ABOUT IT IN A WAY
THAT MATTER TO AMERICAN MOTORS.
I THINK CANDIDATES THAT ARE
ABOUT TO ENTER THE FIELD I THINK
BETO O'ROURKE COULD BE A HAVE A
PARTY THAT WANTS TO CHANGE THE
PAGE AND MOVE FORWARD.
I THINK HE CAN BE A TREMENDOUS
CANDIDATE.
I THINK WE HAVE A TREMENDOUS
FIELD OF CANDIDATES OUT THERE.
LOOK.
I THINK YOU KNOW THE NBC POLL
SHOWS TRUMP IS IN A ROCKY PLACE
TO BEGIN THE FINAL TWO YEARS AND
RE-ELECTION CAMPAIGN.
ONLY 41% OF THE PUBLIC WANT TO
VOTE FOR HIS RE-ELECTION.
SO THAT'S A TOUGH PLACE FOR HIM
TO BE IN.
I THINK WE HAVE A GREAT FIELD OF
CANDIDATES WITH POWERFUL
MESSAGES.
I'M VERY OPTIMISTIC WE CAN
DEFEAT TRUMP IN 2020.
>> COULD I LET YOU GO, THE LAST
SIME TIME SANDERS RAN FOR
PRESIDENT, DID HE EVER GO ABOUT
DISTINGUISHING HIMSELF FROM
OTHER CANDIDATES NOW THAT MIGHT
HAVE SIMILAR POLICIES?
>> I THINK IT'S A TESTAMENT TO
SENATOR SANDERS THAT MUCH OF THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY HAS MOVED IN
HIS DIRECTION.
I WILL SAY I THINK THE PARTY WAS
MOVING TO THE LEFT OVER THE LAST
DECADE.
IT WAS ONE OF THE THINGS WE SAW
AS WE WENT INTO THE LAST
CAMPAIGN.
I'M NOT SURE EVERYBODY
RECOGNIZED THE DEGREE THEY WERE
MOVING TO THE LEFT.
A LOT OF CANDIDATES HAVE MOVED
INTO THAT SPACE ONLY MAKES SENSE
BECAUSE THAT'S WHERE ELECTORATE
IS.
IS HE ONLY A GRASS ROOTS GUY?
>> I THINK HE IS A GRASS ROOTS
GUY.
KAMELA HARRIS WAS EFFECTIVE IN
THE FIRST 24 HOURS OF HER
CANDIDACY RAISING MONEY.
LIKE I SAY, I THINK BETO
O'ROURKE SHOULD HE GET IN, HE
DISPLAYED IN TEXAS THE LAST
GO-AROUND A HUGE ABILITY TO
RAISE MONEY FROM SMALL DONORS
AND ONLINE.
I THINK SEVERAL OF THESE
CANDIDATES WILL BE VERY, VERY
COMPETITIVE IN TERMS OF THEIR
ABILITY TO MUSTER GRASS ROOTS
SUPPORT.
I WILL SAY AS THEY CAMPAIGN
ACROSS IOWA, NEW HAMPSHIRE,
SOUTH CAROLINA, THEY'RE ALL
DRAWING GREAT CROWDS, SO I THINK
IT'S A PART OF THE ENTHUSIASM OF
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY AND THE
DESIRE TO GET RID OF DONALD
TRUMP AND WHERE HIS PARTY IS
HEADED.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> YES, ABSOLUTELY.
>>> FOR PAUL MANAFORT, IT'S ONE
DAY OF RECKONING IN THE BOOKS,
STILL ANOTHER ONE TO BE WRITTEN.
HOW WILL NEXT WEEK GO FOR THE
DISGRACED CAMPAIGN CHAIRMAN?
E
y ge
when you can stay home
with Neulasta Onpro?
Strong chemo can put you at
risk of serious infection.
In a key study Neulasta
reduced the risk of infection
from 17% to 1%,
a 94% decrease.
Neulasta Onpro is designed
to deliver Neulasta
the day after chemo
and is used by most patients
today.
Neulasta is for certain
cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta if you're
allergic to it
or Neupogen (filgrastim).
An incomplete dose could
increase infection risk.
Ruptured spleen,
sometimes fatal as well as
serious lung problems,
allergic reactions,
kidney injuries and capillary
leak syndrome have occurred.
Report abdominal or shoulder
tip pain, trouble breathing
or allergic reactions to
your doctor right away.
In patients with sickle
cell disorders,
serious, sometimes fatal crises
can occur.
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
If you'd rather be home,
ask your doctor about
Neulasta Onpro.
Pay no more than $5 per dose
with copay card.
.
>>> THERE ARE NEW QUESTIONS
TODAY ABOUT THE FUTURE OF THE
CAMPAIGN CHAIRMAN AFTER THE
PRESIDENT'S REMARKS THAT SEEMED
TO LEAVE A PARDON ON THE TABLE.
LET'S ALL TAKE A LISTEN TO IT.
>> I FEEL VERY BADLY FOR PAUL
MANAFORT.
THE JUDGE SAID THERE WAS NO
COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA I DON'T
EVEN DISCUSS IT.
THE ONLY ONE DISCUSSING IT IS
YOU.
I HAVEN'T DISCUSSED IT.
>> THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S OFFICE
NEVER RECOMMENDED A SPECIFIC
SENTENCE.
GUIDELINES CALLED FOR 19 TO 24
YEARS.
HE WAS SENTENCED TO 47 MONTHS,
NOT EVEN FOUR YEARS.
JOINING ME IS A PROFESSOR OF
LAW, RATHER, AT THE UNIVERSITY
OF MEMPHIS, STEVEN MULROY, THE
AUTHOR OF "RETHINKING THE
ELECTION LAW."
SIR, WELCOME TO YOU.
WERE YOU SURPRISED BY THE
LENIENCE OF THIS SENTENCE?
BECAUSE MICHAEL COHEN, LET'S
POINT OUT, WHO HAS BEEN
COOPERATING WITH PROSECUTORS.
HEF GOT THREE YEARS.
RIGHT?
>> RIGHT.
>> THAT'S A YEAR LESS THAN
MANAFORT WHO WENT OUT OF HIS WAY
TO IMPEDE THE INVESTIGATION AND
LIED.
>> YES.
THE DISPARITY BETWEEN THE TWO IS
SOMEWHAT STRIKING ESPECIALLY
BECAUSE AFTER AGREEING TO A PLEA
AGREEMENT, MANAFORT THEN
VIOLATED THAT BY LYING TO
FEDERAL PROSECUTORS AND ENGAGING
IN WITNESS TAMPERING SO MUCH SO
HE IS NOW IN CUSHION TOAD IN
JAIL AWAITING HIS SENTENCE.
I THINK THAT YOU KNOW IT'S ON
ONE HAND SURPRISING BECAUSE OF
THE DISPARITY.
ON THE OTHER HAND, NOT AS
SURPRISING BECAUSE JUDGE ELLIS,
A REAGAN APPOINTEE HAD BEEN
SKEPTICAL ABOUT THIS PROSECUTION
FROM THE GET GO AND MADE
COMMENTS REVEALING THAT
SKEPTICISM.
SO MAYBE IN HINDS SIGHT WE
SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN SURPRISED.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE POSSIBILITY OF
THE PRESIDENT LEAVING A PARDON
FOR MANAFORT?
IS THAT HOW YOU LEAVE IT?
YOU THINK HE'S THINKING, WELL,
MAYBE?
IF HE DOES PARDON HIM, WHAT CAN
WE EXPECT?
>> SO IT MIGHT VERY WELL BE THE
CASE THAT WHETHER TRUMP INTENDS
TO PARDON HIM OR FOUGHT, WHETHER
HE'S MADE UP HIS MIND, YOU KNOW,
HIS LAWYER RUDY GUILIANI SAYS
THAT SNUG IS BEING THOUGHT ABOUT
REGARDING PARDONS.
IT COULD BE THE CASE HE IS
DANGLING THE POSSIBILITY OF A
PARDON OUT THERE.
I KNOW THIS, IF THERE IS A
PARDON GRANTED, THERE IS AN
INVESTIGATION RIGHT NOW BY THE
MANHATTAN DISTRICT ATTORNEY ON
STATE LEVEL FRAUD CHARGES AND
TAX AVOIDANCE CHARGES AND THOSE
CHARGES COULD NOT BE AFFECTED BY
A PRESIDENTIAL PARDON.
>> OKAY.
WLOOBT THE PRESIDENT'S CLAIM --
WHAT ABOUT THE PRESIDENT'S
CLAIM, YOU HARD IT THERE.
THE JUDGE, JUDGE ELLIS, SAID
THERE WAS NO COLLUSION WITH
RUSSIA.
LET'S TAKE A LISTEN TO THIS ONE
MORE TIME.
>> THE JUDGE SAID THERE WAS NO
COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA.
IT'S HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
COLLUSION.
THERE WAS NO COLLUSION.
IT'S A COLLUSION HOAX.
IT'S A COLLUSION WITCH HOAX.
I DON'T CLUED WITH RUSSIA.
THE JUDGE, I MEAN FOR WHATEVER
REASON, I WAS VERY HONORED BY IT
ALSO MADE THIS STATEMENT THAT
THIS HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA.
>> SO THE PRESIDENT IS MIXING
THINGS UP SHEER.
ACCORDING TO COURT TRANSCRIPT,
THE TRUTH IS THE JUDGE SAID
MANAFORT IS NOT BEFORE THE COURT
FOR ANY ALLEGATION THAT HE OR
ANYBODY AT HIS DIRECTION CLUED
WITH THE JUDGMENT.
HE PUTS THIS TOGETHER THE JUDGE
SAID THERE WAS NO COLLUSION.
WHAT DOES THE GOVERNMENT AND THE
CASE FILINGS SUGGEST TO YOU ON
ALL THIS?
>> I MEAN YOU ARE EXACTLY RIGHT.
HE IS MIXING UP THE FEDERAL
COURT DID NOT HAVE AN ELECTION
JUDGE ELLIS MADE THAT POINT BUT
THAT DOES NOT MEAN THE JUDGE
WEIGHED IN ON COLLUSION, HE
DIDN'T SPEAK TO IT AT ALL.
TO CORN PLATE THE TWO IS
OBVIOUSLY GROSSLY MISLEADING.
>> OKAY.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
SEE YOU AGAIN, THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> IT IS THE BEST IMPACT
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS HAVING ON THE
2020 CAMPAIGN SO FAR.
DOES IT CLUE US IN ON WHO WILL
WIN THE WHITE HOUSE?
>>> NOW TO SOARING DEMOCRATIC
ENTHUSIASM STILL A YEAR OUT TO
FROM 2020 PRIMARIES.
CANDIDATES ARE PACKING ONE
CAMPAIGN STOP AFTER ANOTHER.
THE "NEW YORK TIMES" IS OUT WITH
A NEW LOOK AT THE BEAT TRUMP
VERROR AND REPORTS WHILE THE
ENERGY HAS BEEN UPLIFTING FOR
MANY CANDIDATES IT POSED
SOMEWHAT OF A CHALLENGE TO STAGE
EARLY STAGE POPULARITY.
JOINING ME NOW, BILL PRESS, TALK
SHOW HOST DANIEL MOODY MILLS AND
NSNBC POLITICAL ANALYST.
GLAD TO SEE ALL OF YOU.
STILL, LADIES FIRST, PUT THIS IN
PERSPECTIVE.
THIS HIGH LEVEL INTEREST IN SO
MANY DIFFERENT CANDIDATES.
>> I THINK DEMOCRATS ARE VERY
EXCITED RIGHT NOW ABOUT HAVING
REAL SUBSTANTIVE POLICY
QUESTIONS THAT CANDIDATES ARE
BRINGING TO THE TABLE RIGHT NOW.
THEY'RE ALL STRONG CONTENDERS.
I'M NOT SURE WHO AT THIS VERY
MOMENT I SEE ON THE DEBATE STAGE
WITH
I THINK THE TURNOUT PEOPLE ARE
SEEING, WHETHER THEY BE TOWN
HALLS, BIG STREET RALLIES IS
VERY EXCITING AND I THINK THAT
IT IS GOING TO HELP US CARRY ON
FORWARD TO 2020 WITH A LOT OF
FERVOR.
>> I DON'T THINK EITHER OF THE
GENTLEMEN BESIDE YOU WOULD PUT
TRUMP AT THE TABLE WHEN IT IS
SAID AND DONE.
BILL, TALKING ABOUT THE STANDARD
GAUGES FOR EXCITEMENT, CROWD
SIZE AND NOISE, BUT IT IS
DIFFICULT TO DISTINGUISH
CANDIDATES.
HOW DO YOU THINK CANDIDATES ARE
EVALUATING CAMPAIGNS IN EARLY
DAYS?
>> ALEX, WE HAVEN'T EVEN HAD THE
FIRST DEBATE YET.
THERE'S A LONG WAY TO GO.
IN 2018 THERE'S NO DOUBT, THE
ENERGY AND MOMENTUM, ENTHUSIASM
WAS ON THE DEMOCRATIC SIDE,
THERE WERE MORE DEMOCRATS
RUNNING FOR OFFICE THAN BEFORE,
TURNOUT WAS HIGHER THAN BEFORE,
AND LOOK WHAT HAPPENED.
40 NEW MEMBERS IN THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES, I THINK SEVEN
GOVERNORS ACROSS THE BOARD,
HUNDREDS OF NEW STATE DEMOCRATIC
LEGISLATORS.
THAT ENERGY IS CONTINUING INTO
2020.
THE FIELD IS CROWDED.
WE KNOW THERE COULD BE MORE
COMING IN, JOE BIDEN IS ON THE
VERGE OF IT, MAYBE TERRY
McCAULIFFE, BETO O'ROURKE, IT
WILL TAKE TIME FOR THAT FIELD TO
SORT OUT.
NO DOUBT IT IS PAYING OFF IN
TERMS OF HUGE CROWDS, SMALL
DOLLAR DONATIONS UNHEARD OF
BEFORE, AND IT IS AS LONG AS
DEMOCRATS DON'T GET TOO COCKY,
THEY HAVE A GOOD SHOT AT 2020.
>> INTERESTING POINT, THAT LAST
NIGHT.
LET'S GO TO YOU, RICK.
THERE'S A "THE WASHINGTON POST"
COLUMN THAT'S TITLED EVERYONE IS
UNDERESTIMATING TRUMP, IT COULD
HURT DEMOCRATS AND REPUBLICANS
ALIKE.
IN THIS ARTICLE IT ARGUES THAT
REPUBLICANS SHOULD MAKE SURE
THEY HAVE A PLAN FOR WHAT TO DO
IF TRUMP WINS IN 2020.
GIVEN THAT IT WILL BE HARDER FOR
THE REST OF THE GOP TO ARGUE
WITH THE TRUMPISTS.
WHAT'S YOUR TAKE ON THIS?
>> I THINK THAT'S RIGHT.
LOOK, TRUMP DOES NOT HAVE HIGH
POPULARITY, BUT PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO JUDGE THE 2020 CAMPAIGN BASED
ON THEIR OWN ECONOMIC
CONDITIONS.
THAT'S ALWAYS BEEN TRUE.
AND IF THEY BELIEVE THAT
CANDIDATES ARE GOING TO SOMEHOW
HURT THE ECONOMY, LET'S
STIPULATE THAT TRUMP DOESN'T
LEAD US INTO SOME NATIONAL
DISASTER OR THE ECONOMY DOESN'T
TANK BETWEEN NOW AND 2020 AND
THE ECONOMY CONTINUES TO BE GOOD
AND UNEMPLOYMENT IS LOW, THAT'S
A TOUGH CASE TO MAKE, DESPITE
TRUMP THAT PEOPLE ARE GOING TO
WANT TO FEEL SECURE THE ECONOMY
WILL KEEP GOING.
THE ECONOMY KEEPS GOING FOR FOUR
YEARS OF TRUMP, THEY'RE GOING TO
MAKE A CASE.
TAKE ELIZABETH WARREN.
SHE TALKED ABOUT BREAKING UP
FACEBOOK, GOOGLE, APPLE, AND
AMAZON.
BUT I SHOULD REMIND VIEWERS THAT
THE COMBINED VALUATION OF ALL
THOSE COMPANIES IS ONE-EIGHTH OF
WHAT THE GOVERNMENT SPENDS EVERY
YEAR.
IT IS A $4 TRILLION ENTERPRISE.
IN FACT, IT OVERSPENDS EVERY
YEAR TWICE THE VALUATION OF ALL
THOSE COMPANIES, SO HOW IS
ELIZABETH WARREN TELLING US THAT
SHE WANTS TO MEDDLE IN PRIVATE
SECTOR SUCCESSFUL COMPANIES WHEN
IN FACT SHE SUPPORTS THE VERY
POLICIES THAT CREATED THOSE
CONSOLIDATIONS, NOT ONLY IN THE
TECH AND BANKING INDUSTRY,
BECAUSE SHE RAISES THE COST OF
COMPLIANCE, KEEPING DOWN FUTURE
COMPETITORS, SO ALL THAT MONEY
IS CHASING COMPLIANCE AND NOT
INNOVATION.
BIG COMPANIES LOVE ELIZABETH
WARREN, THEY CAN AFFORD THE
COMPLIANCE, SMALL COMPETITORS
CAN'T.
>> FOR THOSE THAT HAVEN'T HEARD
THAT SOUND BITE, LET'S PLAY
ELIZABETH WARREN.
AND DANIELLE I'LL HAVE YOU REACT
TO IT.
HERE IT IS.
WE DON'T HAVE THE SOUND BITE.
YOU MADE A GOOD POINT, YOU
ARTICULATED IT WELL, RICK.
DANIELLE, YOUR THOUGHTS ABOUT
THIS, IS IT SMART FOR ELIZABETH
WARREN TO DO THAT, CREATING
SPECIFIC TARGETS AS SHE
CONTINUES TO TAKE ON BIG MONEY?
>> I THINK IT IS ABSOLUTELY ON
BRAND FOR ELIZABETH WARREN TO BE
SAYING THAT SHE'S GOING TO TAKE
ON BIG BUSINESS, THAT SHE HAS
BEEN ONE OF THE CANDIDATES
THAT'S BEEN OUT FRONT, TALKING
ABOUT RACIAL WEALTH GAP AND
WEALTH DISPARITY, HOW UNBALANCED
OUR ECONOMIC SYSTEM IS.
GIVEN WHAT JUST TRANSPIRED
AROUND AMAZON IN NEW YORK AND
DECIDING NOT TO COME, REGARDLESS
OF ALL OF THE TAX INCENTIVES
THAT ARE BEING THROWN AT THEM,
WITHOUT ANY GUARANTEE OF WHETHER
OR NOT THEY WERE GOING TO
ACTUALLY EMPLOY PEOPLE THAT WERE
IN NEW YORK FOR SUSTAINABLE
UNEMPLOYMENT AT AMAZON, THERE
WERE A LOT OF THINGS THAT ARE
GIVEN TO COMPANIES WITHOUT A LOT
OF RETURN.
I THINK WHAT ELIZABETH WARREN IS
BRINGING UP TO THE SURFACE IS WE
CAN'T GET INTO A SITUATION WE
DID WITH THE BANKS, RIGHT, AND
COMPANIES THAT ARE TOO BIG TO
FAIL, THAT WE NEED TO PUT ALL
OUR RESOURCES, GIVE THEM
EVERYTHING THEY NEED BECAUSE NOW
CITIES AND STATES ARE AT THE
WILL OF BIG TECH COMPANIES AND
WHAT THEY WANT AND NEED.
I THINK THERE NEEDS TO BE SOME
TYPE OF TRANSPARENCY, SOME TYPE
OF OVERSIGHT BECAUSE THEY'RE
GETTING BIGGER AND BIGGER AND
BIGGER, AND ELIZABETH WARREN IS
WELL AWARE OF WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
YOU ALLOW COMPANIES TO RUN
AMUCK, RIGHT, AND GO
UNCHALLENGED BECAUSE OH, THEY'RE
THE BIGGEST EMPLOYERS.
>> SO BILL, DID YOU HEAR THE
EXCHANGE ON MORNING JOE WITH
HICKENLOOPER?
>> I DID.
>> AND HICKENLOOPER HAD A HARD
TIME SELF IDENTIFYING AS A
CAPITALIST, SAYING HE BELIEVED
IN CAPITALISM.
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS ON THAT?
>> LET ME JUST SAY, I DIDN'T
THINK JOHN HICKENLOOPER WAS A
SERIOUS CONTENDER, NOW I KNOW
HE'S NOT OR CERTAINLY NOT READY
FOR PRIME TIME.
LOOK, WE KNOW THERE HAVE TO BE
LIMITS ON, RESTRICTIONS ON GOOD
REGULATIONS, NO CHILD LABOR,
GOOD STRONG ENVIRONMENTAL
PROTECTION, BUT I DON'T THINK
ANY OF US SHOULD HESITATE TO SAY
WE ARE A CAPITALIST OR THAT
CAPITALISM WORKS, IT IS OUR
SYSTEM.
IT WORKED FOR A LONG TIME.
PROPERLY REGULATED, PROPERLY
CONTAINED, NOTHING WRONG IN
SAYING YES, I'M A CAPITALIST.
>> RICK, I WANT TO GET PERSONAL
BEFORE WE WRAP IT UP.
I WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT THE
ARTICLE IN THE "DAILY BEAST,"
TITLED VENFUL TRUMP IS BLACK
BAWLING DISLOIL CONSERVATIVE
OPERATIVES LIKE RICK TYLER.
IS IT IMPACTING YOUR WORK?
YOU GAVE ME A POWERFUL SOUND
BITE LAST SATURDAY, AND I
REITERATED IT MANY TIMES, PLAYED
IT OTHER TIMES THROUGH THE
WEEKEND.
>> I WAS HONORED TO BE BLACK
BALD BY THE TRUMP WHITE HOUSE.
AND THIS TOO SHALL PASS.
ALL I WAS TRYING TO DO IS GET
GOOD CONSERVATIVES ELECTED TO
CONGRESS.
DONALD TRUMP DOESN'T WANT GOOD
CONSERVATIVES ELECTED, THAT'S
HIS CHOICE.
HE'LL MOVE ON.
>> THAT'S IT.
GOOD TO SEE YOU GUYS.
THANK YOU.
>>> TEN YEARS OF TAX RETURNS,
WHAT DEMS WANT FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE.
RETURNS,
WHAT DEMS WANT FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE.
With Fidelity Wealth Management
you get straightforward advice,
tailored recommendations,
tax-efficient
investing strategies,
and a dedicated advisor
to help you grow
and protect your wealth.
Fidelity Wealth Management.
I don't keep
track of regrets.
to help you grow
and protect your wealth.
And I don't add
up the years.
But what I do count on...
is BOOST®
Delicious BOOST® High
Protein Nutritional Drink
has 20 grams of protein,
along with 26 essential
vitamins and minerals.
BOOST® High Protein.
Be Up for Life.
First tattoo?
Yeah
Relax, Amigo, it's gonna
look OK.
Only OK?
No worries boss, I'm one of THE
tattoo artists in the city.
You mean one of the best tattoo
artists in the city? Right?
Something like that... ya.
Uh, aren't you supposed to draw
it first?
Stay in your lane, bro.
JUST OK IS NOT OK.
Especially when it comes to
your network.
AT&T is America's best wireless
network,
according to America's biggest
test.
Buy a new Samsung Galaxy S10