REMAIN.
BUT FOR A MAN WHO GAMBLED ON
OTHER PEOPLE'S FATE, CONTROLLING
HIS OWN DESTINY WAS HIS SAFEST
BET.
>> HE'S JUST THIS ICONIC TYPE
OF FIGURE IN AMERICA OF THE
IMMIGRANT WHO LOOKS LIKE HE'S
MAKING GOOD, BUT IN FACT, YOU
KNOW, THE WHOLE THING WAS BASED
ON A FALSE UNDERPINNING, AND IT
OBVIOUSLY CAME CRASHING DOWN.
>>> HI, EVERYONE, WELCOME TO "ON
THE MONEY.
I'M BECKY QUICK.
A HELPING HAND FOR THOSE
STRUGGLING TO MAKE ENDS MEET,
AND ONE THING THAT COULD MAKE A
BIG DIFFERENCE IN THEIR LIVES.
>> THE RATE OF POVERTY HERE IS
THREE TIMES WHAT YOU SEE IN THE
NATION AS A WHOLE.
>>> IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A JOB,
NOW IS A GOOD TIME
IF YOU'RE HIRING, MAYBE NOT.
THE SKILLS EMPLOYERS WANT, AND
HOW YOU CAN INCREASE YOUR VALUE.
YOU MAY NOT HAVE TO DO THAT IF
YOU'RE A HEALTH CARE WORKER.
IF YOU LIKE LIGHTS, SIRENS, AND
SAVING LIVES, THERE COULD BE A
CAREER FOR YOU
>>> AND WILL GIVING DOGS PEOPLE
FOOD MAKE THEM HEALTHIER AND
HAPPIER?
ONE COMPANY IS BETTING THE FARM
ON IT.
"ON THE MONEY" STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> THIS IS "ON THE MONEY," YOUR
MONEY, YOUR LIFE, YOUR FUTURE.
NOW, BECKY QUICK
>> WE BEGIN WITH A STORY THAT
MOST PEOPLE DON'T KNOW ABOUT BUT
SHOULD
A STAGGERING NUMBER-- ONE IN
FOUR U.S. HOUSEHOLDS ARE
ACTUALLY NDERBANKED OR
UNBANKED
THAT MEANS THEY EITHER DON'T
HAVE A BANK ACCOUNT OR HAVE ONE
BUT STILL NEED TO USE EXPENSIVE
SERVICES LIKE PAYDAY LOANS JUST
TO MAKE ENDS MEET.
STEVE LEASEMAN DUG INTO THIS
IN THE MISSISSIPPI DELTA, HE
FOUND THE STORY OF A FAMILY, A
FIRE, AND A FOCUS ON THE
FINANCIAL SYSTEM
>> Reporter: TWO FIRES IN THEIR
HOMES IN THE MISSISSIPPI DELTA
LEFT FARRAH APPLEBURY AND HER
GIRLS DESTITUTE.
>> WE PRAYED IN UNISON BECAUSE I
DIDN'T WANT TO LOSE ANOTHER
HOME
AND ONE OF MY GIRLS SAID, "MAMA,
IT'S GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT
GOD GOT US," THAT THIS, TOO,
SHALL PASS
>> Reporter: ALONG LITERALLY
CAME HOPE.
A CREDIT UNION FOCUSED ON
ECONOMICALLY DISTRESSED AREAS IN
THE SOUTH THAT BRINGS BASIC
BANKING SERVICES TO THE NATION'S
POOREST.
>> THE RATE OF POVERTY HERE IS
THREE TIMES WHAT YOU SEE IN THE
NATION AS A WHOLE, EVEN GREATER
FOR THE REGION'S
AFRICAN-AMERICAN RESIDENTS
IF YOU LOOK AT LEVEL OF BANKING
SERVICES, THREE TIMES THE LEVEL
OF PEOPLE WHO DON'T HAVE A
BANKING ACCOUNT.
AND WHEN YOU ADD THE NUMBER OF
PEOPLE WHO USE CHECK CASHERS AND
PAYDAY LENDERS, BETWEEN 60% TO
70% OF THE MEMBERS WHO JOIN OUR
CREDIT UNION WERE OUTSIDE THE
BANKING SYSTEM OR ON THE EDGE OF
THE FINANCIAL SYSTEM, PAYING
HIGH RATES OR DID NOT HAVE BASIC
TOOLS TO SUPPORT THEIR FAMILIES
AND STABILIZE THEIR FINANCIAL
LIVES.
>> Reporter: YOU CAN SEE THE
ABSENCE OF BANKING SERVICES IN
POOR TOWNS LIKE THIS THROUGHOUT
THE MISSISSIPPI DELTA.
NATIONALLY, ONE IN FOUR
AMERICANS IS ESTIMATED TO BE
UNBANKED OR UNDERBANKED, MEANING
THEY DON'T HAVE ACCESS TO BASIC
BANKING SERVICES
SOME LIVE IN BANKING DESERTS
WHERE THERE JUST AREN'T BRANCHES
FOR MILES.
SOME DON'T TRUST BANKS, AND SOME
THINK THEY'RE JUST TOO POOR TO
OPEN AN ACCOUNT.
BUT THERE'S ALSO MORE FOCUS ON
THE ISSUE.
RECENTLY FED CHAIRMAN JEROME
POWELL MADE AN HISTORIC TRIP TO
THE DELTA, SPEAKING TO STUDENTS
AND ATTENDING A CONFERENCE WITH
INVESTORS, BANKERS, AND
COMMUNITY ACTIVISTS TO SHINE A
SPOTLIGHT ON THE PROBLEM OF THE
UNBANKED
>> ACCESS TO SAFE AND AFFORDABLE
FINANCIAL SERVICES IS VITAL,
ESPECIALLY AMONG FAMILIES WITH
LIMITED WEALTH
WHETHER THEY'RE LOOKING TO
INVEST IN EDUCATION, START A
BUSINESS, OR SIMPLY MANAGE THE
UPS AND DOWNS OF LIFE.
>> Reporter: ACCESS TO BANKING
IS SUCH A PROBLEM DOWN HERE THAT
IT WAS ONLY IN 2015 THAT HOPE
OPENED THE TOWN'S FIRST BANK
ATM.
>> WHEN HOPE CAME IN, THEY --
THAT WAS THE FIRST THING THEY
DID.
THEY KNOCKED A HOLE IN THE WALL
AND PUT AN ATM MACHINE THERE
THERE WAS VERY LITTLE BUSINESS
THAT YOU COULD CONDUCT HERE IN
MOORHEAD
>> Reporter: FINANCIAL
COUNSELING MEANS FARRAH SHOULD
BE OUT OF BANKRUPTCY BY
NOVEMBER
>> ONCE I GET OUT OF BANKRUPTCY,
I KNOW IT MAY NOT BE THE FATTEST
ACCOUNT, BUT I'M LOOKING TO HAVE
ENOUGH MONEY IN HOPE THAT IF I
HAVE A DRY DAY, ME AND MY GIRLS
WILL STILL MAKE IT
SO I HAD TO LEARN TO SAVE SMALL
TO GET TO BE
>> Reporter: FOR THE UNBANKED
TRYING TO FIND THEIR WAY OUT OF
POVERTY, SOME ACCOUNT, NO MATTER
WHAT SIZE, IS BETTER THAN NO
ACCOUNT AT ALL
AND FINANCIAL EXPERTS SAY MRS.
APPLEBERRY IS RIGHT.
ANY ACCOUNT NO MATTER HOW SMALL
IS BETTER THAN NONE.
THE GROWING CHALLENGE --
COMMUNITY BANKS ARE CLOSING,
TECHNOLOGY'S ELIMINATING THE
NEED FOR BRANCHES.
MOREAND MORE, POOR COMMUNITIES
HAVE LESS AND LESS ACCESS TO THE
BANKING SERVICES THEY NEED,
BECKY.
>> WHEN I'VE TALKED TO OTHER
PEOPLE, THEY SAY, YES, BUT YOU
CAN DO SO MUCH WITH YOUR PHONE
YOU CAN DO ALL OF THOSE THINGS
THERE.
HOW COME THAT DOESN'T TRANSLATE
TO HELPING PEOPLE IN COMMUNITIES
WHERE THEY NEED IT
>> TECHNOLOGY CREATES A PROMISE,
BUT YOU HAVE TO LEAP OVER THE
IDEA THAT SOME OF THEM DON'T
HAVE BANKING ACCOUNTS, RIGHT
THE IDEA THAT YOU CAN DO SO MUCH
WITH THIS PHONE AND YET SOME
PEOPLE DON'T EVEN HAVE ACCESS
TTO
ATMs, TO BRIDGE THE TECHNOLOGY
BANKS ARE CLOSING DOWN, MANY ARE
GOING AWAY
SO THE MORE TECHNOLOGY GOES
FORWARD, THE MORE THESE PEOPLE
GET LEFT BEHIND.
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE THE COMMUNITY
BANKS ALSO PROVIDE SOMETHING, A
LITTLE COUNSELING ALMOST, TO
WALK YOU THROUGH THE IT.
YOU NEED THAT PERSONAL TOUCH
>> ABSOLUTELY.
ON THE BROADER LEVEL, BECKY,
BANKING AND LENDING IS BECOMING
A COMMODITY.
YOU CAN GO ON LINE AND FILL OUT
A FORM TO GET A LOAN, AND YOU
CAN GET AN ANSWER WHEN YOU HIT
ENTER.
IT'S COMMODITIZED BASED ON YOUR
INCOME AND CREDIT STORY.
PEOPLE LIKE MS. APPLEBERRY NEED
INDIVIDUAL COUNSELING.
THE WAY THEY LOOK AT HER AND
OTHER LENDING THERE IS PIECE BY
PIECE.
SOME CASES THEY USE CABLE BILLS
TO SHOW YOUR FINANCIAL --
ABILITY TO REPAY
THAT ONE-ON-ONE SERVICE IS GOING
AWAY IN THE BROADER BANKING
BUSINESS
>> THANK YOU
AN EXCELLENT STORY
I'M GLAD YOU BROUGHT IT TO US.
>> THANK YOU
>> STEVE LEASEMAN.
>>> HOPE CREDIT UNION IS ONE OF
NEARLY 1,200 COMMUNITY
DEVELOPMENT FINANCIAL
INSTITUTIONS OR CDFIs, THAT ARE
IMPROVING COMMUNITIES AND
PROVIDING THE UNDERBANKED AND
UNBANKED ACCESS TO MAINSTREAM
FINANCE.
JOINING US IS LISA MENSA,
PRESIDENT AND CEO OF THE
OPPORTUNITY FINANCE NETWORK.
LISA, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
BEING HERE
>> THANK YOU
>> YOUR ORGANIZATION DOES THIS
YOU HELP CDFIs SO THEY CAN
PROVIDE AFFORDABLE SERVICES LIKE
THIS
HOW DOES IT WORK
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE HELP GET THE MONEY, AMPLIFY
THE VOICE AND STRENGTHEN THE
NATION'S COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT
FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONS
WE'RE ABOUT 1,200 ACROSS THE
NATION
WE MANAGE ABOUT $150 BILLION IN
ASSETS COLLECTIVELY.
AND OUR JOB IS TO HELP THOSE
CREDIT UNIONS AND LOAN FUNDS AND
COMMUNITY BANKS DO MORE, HELP
MORE PEOPLE, SO THAT THEY CAN
MOVE ON WITH THEIR LIVES
>> IT'S KIND OF A STAGGERING
STATISTIC WHEN YOU'RE THINKING
THAT 25%, ONE IN FOUR HOUSEHOLDS
ARE ACTUALLY IN NEED OF
ADDITIONAL BANKING
THEY'RE UNBANKED OR UNDERBANKED.
WHAT -- WHAT HAPPENED, IS THIS
UNUSUAL, WHEN WE DIG INTO THIS,
WHAT ARE THE REASONS BEHIND WHY
THEY DON'T HAVE BANK ACCOUNTS?
>> YEAH.
IT'S BOTH PERSONAL AND SYSTEMIC.
AND I THINK THAT'S WHAT THIS
STORY IN MISSISSIPPI SHOWED.
WE'RE SO GLAD THAT CHAIRMAN
POWELL PUT A SPOTLIGHT ON THIS
IN SOME CASES, IT'S PERSONAL
THERE HAVE BEEN BANKRUPTCIES OR
FIRES OR THINGS.
THE GOOD PART ABOUT WORKING WITH
CDFIs IS THAT CDFIs HELP THE
PEOPLE GET ON WITH THEIR LIVES
BUT ALSO HELP THE PLACES RISE.
YOU ALSO NEED NOT JUST TRANSACT
BUT TO GET READY FOR A MORTGAGE,
TO HELP SEND KIDS TO SCHOOL, AND
TO DO THE THINGS THAT HELP MOVE
YOU INTO THE MIDDLE CLASS.
THAT'S WHERE THESE
MISSION-ORIENTED LOAN FUNDS OR
BANKS OR CREDIT UNIONS ARE VERY
STRONG
>> WHAT YOU SAY, WHERE WE TALK
ABOUT IT BEING A SYSTEMIC
PROBLEM, IT SOUNDS LIKE IT'S
HARD TO BREAK THE CYCLE IF YOU
HAVEN'T SEEN ACCESS TO THIS IN
THE PAST, IF YOU HAVEN'T BEEN
TAUGHT IT IN SCHOOL, IF YOU
HAVEN'T WATCHED IT HAPPEN AT
HOME, IT'S HARD TO FIGURE OUT ON
YOUR OWN
IT'S NOT INTUITIVE, A LOT OF IT.
>> IT'S NOT INTUITIVE.
HAVING A STRONG PARTNER, AN
OLD-FASHIONED COMMUNITY
DEVELOPMENT FINANCIAL
INSTITUTION THAT WILL GIVE YOU
SOME ADVICE, BUT ALSO PROVIDE
YOU WITH AN ACCOUNT SO THAT YOU
START BREAKING THE CYCLE
YOU ACTUALLY GET A GOOD CREDIT
HISTORY.
AND THEY WANT TO BE THERE FOR
THAT NEXT LOAN, FOR THE LOAN FOR
THE HOUSE, THE -- THE HELP FOR
THE COMMUNITY.
WE LIKE TO THINK OF OURSELVES AS
MAYOR'S BEST FRIEND BECAUSE
WE'LL HELP IN OTHER ASPECTS OF
HELPING A COMMUNITY.
>> DO THE CDFIs MAKE MONEY, AS
WELL
IT'S NOT JUST A CHARITABLE
ORGANIZATION, RIGHT?
>> THEY'RE NOT
WE ARE PROFITABLE, BUT WE'RE NOT
PROFIT MAXIMIZING.
WE SEEK TO MAXIMIZE IMPACTS.
WE HELP MORE PEOPLE GET JOBS,
MORE PEOPLE MOVE INTO MORTGAGES.
WE ARE PROFITABLE.
>> HOW DO YOU ACTUALLY BEGIN TO
EDUCATE PEOPLE
IS IT AS EASY AS SETTING UP A
BANK IN A COMMUNITY AND PEOPLE
SUDDENLY START TO TRUST A BANK
THAT MAYBE THEY HAVEN'T TOUCHED
IN THE PAST?
IT SEEMS THAT'S A BIT OF A LEAP.
>> WHAT HOPE DID AND WHAT THAT
CREDIT UNION WAS ABLE TO DO IS
THEY DID SET UP, AND THEY TAKE
TIME WITH PEOPLE
SOMETIMES THIS WAS PEOPLE'S
FIRST ACCOUNT.
THEY HAD A HISTORY OF BEING JUST
WITH PAYDAY LENDERS OR CHECK
CASHERS.
BEING CLOSE ACTUALLY DID START
TO -- ON THE INDIVIDUAL LEVEL.
BUT CDFIs WORK BEYOND THE
INDIVIDUAL LEVEL
WE ACTUALLY ALSO WORK WITH THE
MAYOR, AND WE HELP GET A WHOLE
COMMUNITY'S HOUSING IMPROVED
>> WHAT STEVE TALKED ABOUT, THE
IMPACT OF TECHNOLOGY, THE IDEA
THAT THE FUTURE OF THE BANK
BRANCH IS UNCERTAIN OR -- WHAT
WE KNOW CERTAINLY IS THEY'RE
PROBABLY GOING TO BE -- THERE
ARE PROBABLY GOING TO BE FEWER
AS PEOPLE DO MORE ON LINE, DOES
THAT IMPACT THIS MISSION, AS
WELL
>> IT DOES
SURE, MAINSTREAM BANKING IS
CHANGING, BUT THAT'S WHERE THIS
INDUSTRY, THE CDFI INDUSTRY
WHICH HAS HAD OVER 30 YEARS TO
PRACTICE MAKING GOOD LOANS AND
WORKING WITH INDIVIDUALS AND
WORKING WITH COMMUNITIES, WE'RE
READY NOW TO ACTUALLY DO MORE AS
THE BANKING INDUSTRY CHANGES
SOME FOLKS ARE LEFT OUT, AND
THIS IS WHEN WE'RE PREPARED TO
STEP IN AND HELP MOVE PEOPLE
FORWARD.
>> LISA, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
YOUR TIME TODAY.
>> THANK YOU
>>> UP NEXT, WE ARE "ON THE
MONEY.
IF YOU ARE LOOKING FOR WORK,
EMPLOYERS ARE LOOKING FOR YOU.
THE JOB SKILLS IN HIGHEST
DEMAND
THEY MAY NOT BE EXACTLY WHAT YOU
THINK.
>>> AND LATER, CARING FOR THE
SICK AND INJURED IS A CRITICAL
JOB.
WE RELY ON EMTs TO BE FIRST
RESPONDERS IN AN EMERGENCY
WHY BEING ON CALL CAN BE A
CALLING.
With tough food, your dentures
may slip and fall.
Fixodent Ultra-Max Hold
gives you the strongest hold
ever
to lock your dentures.
So now you can eat tough food
without worry.
Fixodent and forget it.
Guys go through a lot to
deal with shave irritation.
So, we built the
New Gillette SkinGuard
with a specialized guard
designed to reduce it.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
Gillette.
>>> ARE YOU FEELING STUCK IN A
RUT AT WORK?
WELL, GUESS WHAT, NOW MAY BE THE
PERFECT TIME TO LAND THE JOB
THAT YOU HAVE ALWAYS WANTED.
A NEW REPORT FROM CAREER BUILDER
SAYS THAT 40% OF EMPLOYERS PLAN
TO HIRE THIS YEAR.
SENIOR PERSONAL FINANCE
CORRESPONDENT SHARON EPPERSON
JOINS US WITH MORE AND WHAT IT
MEANS FOR YOU IF YOU'RE ON THE
JOB HUNT
GREAT TO SEE YOU
>> GOOD TO BE HERE
>> WHAT ARE THE TOP SKILLS THAT
EMPLOYERS ARE ACTUALLY LOOKING
FOR NOW?
>> A LOT OF FOLKS ARE ON THE JOB
HUNT, AND MANY ARE WORRIED THAT
THEIR SKILLS MAY BE OUTDATED,
MAYBE THEY DON'T KNOW THE LATEST
IN TECHNOLOGY, SO ARE THEY THE
RIGHT CANDIDATE FOR THESE JOBS
CAREER BUILDER FOUND THAT 80% OF
EMPLOYERS SAID SOFT SKILLS ARE
JUST AS IMPORTANT AS HARD SKILLS
--
>> WHAT ARE SOFT SKILLS?
>> MAYBE MORE IMPORTANT.
SOFT SKILLS ARE LIKE GETTING
ALONG WITH OTHER PEOPLE, BEING
ABLE TO WORK ON A TEAM, BEING
ABLE TO PAY ATTENTION TO DETAIL
AND GET THAT TASK DONE, AND
BEING ABLE TO WORK WITH
CUSTOMERS NOT JUST OUTSIDE OF
YOUR COMPANY BUT INSIDE, AS
WELL
>> HOW CAN THEY FIGURE THAT OUT?
WHEN I'M ON AN INTERVIEW WITH
THEM
THAT'S TOUGH
>> THAT'S THEANECDOTES, THE
STORIES THAT YOU TELL.
YOU HAVE TO QUANTIFY IT IN YOUR
RESUME AND COMMUNICATION WITH
THE EMPLOYER
>> WHAT ARE THE AREAS IN
GREATEST DEMAND WHEN IT COMES TO
HIRING FULL-TIME WORKER, AND
WHERE ARE THEY
>> THE GREATEST DEMAND IS FOR
SKILLED LABOR STILL.
BUT THAT'S IN MANY INDUSTRIES,
AND NOT JUST IN MANUFACTURING.
ALSO IMPORTANT, DATA ANALYSIS,
DIGITAL MARKETING,
CYBERSECURITY.
THOSE ARE THE TOP FOUR
>> IF I'M LOOKING AT THAT LIST
AND THINKING HOW DO I GET MYSELF
SOME OF THESE SKILLS, WHAT --
WHAT DO I NEED DO?
>> THE GOOD THING TO KNOW IS YOU
CAN LOOK ANYWHERE IN THE
COUNTRY.
EVEN THOUGH THE WEST AND SOUTH
HAVE MOST OF THOSE JOBS WHERE
THEY'RE HIRING FOR 2019, IT'S
PRETTY WELL SPREAD OUT
THROUGHOUT THE COUNTRY
THAT'S GOOD NEWS
IN TERMS OF HOW TO MAKE YOURSELF
STAND OUT, THERE ARE A COUPLE OF
THINGS YOU NEED DO
FIRST OF ALL, THAT RESUME IS
GOING TO BE KEY.
YOU NEED UPDATE THAT RESUME WITH
NEW SKILLS
HOW DO YOU DO THAT
SAY YOU WANTED TO LEARN SOME
TYPE OF NEW COMPUTER PROGRAMMING
SKILL OR SOFTWARE SKILLS, YOU
CAN TAKE A CLASS ON THAT, OR YOU
CAN WORK ON A PROJECT THAT
ALLOWS YOU TO DO IT.
LEARN BY DOING
SO WHETHER THAT'S VOLUNTEERING
FOR AN ORGANIZATION THAT LETS
YOU DO IT OR FINDING ANOTHER
DEPARTMENT WITHIN YOUR COMPANY
THAT WOULD ALLOW YOU TO WORK ON
SOMETHING, THAT'S ONE OF THE
KEYS YOU WANT TO DO.
YOU TAKE THAT INFORMATION, YOU
PUT IT ON YOUR RESUME.
IT'S EXPERIENCE.
EVEN IF IT'S VOLUNTEER WORK,
IT'S STILL EXPERIENCE IN A KEY
AREA
AND MAKE SURE YOU FIGURE OUT
WHAT THOSE RELEVANT WORDS ARE
THAT THE EMPLOYER IS LOOKING FOR
AND YOU PUT THEM EVERYWHERE, IN
YOUR RESUME, IN YOUR COVER
LETTER
IT'S YOUR SPIN WHEN YOU HAVE THE
INTERVIEW.
AND IT'S ON YOUR LINKEDIN
PROFILE.
THE LAST THING THAT'S IMPORTANT
IS ALWAYS STAY POSITIVE AND
EXUDE CONFIDENCE
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE LIKE I DON'T
KNOW IF I GOT THIS, YOU GOT TO
MAKE SURE THE EMPLOYER THINKS
YOU HAVE IT.
THAT YOU'RE A VALUE, AND THAT
YOU'RE GOING TO ADD VALUE TO THE
COMPANY.
>> GOOD ADVICE
SHARON, THANK YOU.
>> SURE.
>> SHARON EPPERSON
>>> THE SKILLS OF PARAMEDICS AND
EMERGENCY MEDICAL TECHNICIANS
ARE IN HIGH DEMAND
WHETHER THEY'RE RESPONDING TO AN
ACCESS OR ILLNESS, THEIR SPEED
AND ACTIONS SAVE LIVES
MANY RURAL AND URBAN LOCATIONS
ARE FINDING THOSE CRUCIAL JOBS
HARD TO FILL
WE WENT TO MAINE TO FIND OUT
WHY.
[ SIREN
>> Reporter: ON ANY GIVEN DAY,
ERIC MAILMAN COULD TRANSPORT A
BABY, REQUIRING INTENSIVE CARE
FROM ONE HOSPITAL TO ANOTHER, OR
HELP AN ELDERLY PATIENT IN C
CARDIAC ARREST
HE COULD ANSWER BETWEEN FOUR AND
17 CALLS A DAY ON SHIFTS THAT
STRETCH WELL BEYOND 24 HOURS
THE ONLY GUARANTEE IS HIS DAYS
AND NIGHTS WILL BE BUSY AND
UNPREDICTABLE.
>> IF IT'S A SLOW DAY, THEN YOU
-- YOU'RE DOING WELL
THOSE DAYS WHERE THE DEMAND IS
HIGH, YOU HAVE THE INCREASED
CALL VOLUME THAT, YOU KNOW,
EVERYONE DECIDES TO BE SICK ALL
AT ONE TIME, THEN YOU'RE REALLY
-- YOU'RE REALLY STRUGGLING.
>> Reporter: MAILMAN WORKS AT
NORTHERN LIGHT HEALTH WHERE 170
PEOPLE ARE EMPLOYED IN EMERGENCY
MEDICAL SERVICES
BUT THE RURAL MAIN SYSTEM IS IN
NEED OF ABOUT 10% MORE EMS
STAFFERS, AND HIRING IS PROVING
INCREASINGLY CHALLENGING
IN A TIGHT LABOR MARKET ARE
FEWER PEOPLE ARE ENTER THE
PROFESSION
>> UNEMPLOYMENT IS LOW
THAT'S A BIG PART OF IT.
THIS IS A JOB THAT PEOPLE USED
TO GET INTO, YOU KNOW, ONE OF
THE MORE COMMON PATHWAYS WAS
THROUGH VOLUNTEERISM
AND VOLUNTEER YIRK --
VOLUNTEERISM IS WAY DOWN
>> Reporter: SOME 37,000 EMT AND
PARAMEDIC JOBS WILL BE ADDED
THROUGH 2026 ACCORDING TO BLS.
DEMAND FOR EMS WORKERS COMES AT
A TIME WHEN THE HEALTH CARE
SECTOR IS ADDING A MYRIAD OF
JOBS
SOME 42,000 WERE ADDED IN
JANUARY AS THE POPULATION
CONTINUES TO AGE AND SEEK CARE,
AND WORKERS AGE OUT OF THEIR
ROLES IN THE INDUSTRY.
A STRONG JOB MARKET IS ALSO
HAVING ANOTHER EFFECT.
>> MORE PEOPLE WITH HEALTH
BENEFITS, MORE PEOPLE WITH
INSURANCE INCREASES DEMAND FOR
HEALTH CARE.
AND THEREFORE, HEALTH JOBS
>> Reporter: ONE THING IS FOR
SURE -- AS MORE PEOPLE SEEK
CARE, WORKERS LIKE MAILMAN WILL
BE READY TO ANSWER THE CALL.
>> YOU GET TO STEP INTO THE
CHAOS OF THE WORST DAY OF
SOMEBODY'S LIFE AND BRING CALM,
BRING PEACE, AND HAVE THE
ABILITY TO STEP IN AND HELP
SOMEBODY ON THEIR WORST DAY.
THAT TO ME IS PRICELESS.
>> Reporter: BEYOND A WORKER
SHORTAGE, THERE'S A FUNDING
ISSUE FOR PROGRAMS
SOME COMMUNITIES AS
REIMBURSEMENTS FROM INSURERS AND
MEDICAID AND MEDICARE ARE
OUTPACED BY WAGE PRESSURES AND
COSTS TO OPERATE
THIS CAN BE COMMON IN VOLUNTEER
PROGRAMS FUNDED LARGELY BY
DONATIONS AND TAXPAYER DOLLARS
>> WHAT ARE THE PAY AND BENEFITS
SITUATIONS FOR WORKERS LIKE
THIS
>> THEY'LL CERTAINLY VARY.
BUT ON AVERAGE, I THINK PAY WAS
AROUND $30,000 A YEAR, $33,000 A
YEAR, THE MEDIAN PAY
>> WOW
YOU'RE EXPECTED TO BE TRAINED
BEFORE YOU WALK IN THE DOOR BY
VOLUNTEERING YOUR TIME TO GET
THAT DONE.
THAT'S A BIG ASK
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
AND ALSO, THOUGH, DEPENDING
WHERE YOU WORK, SOME OF THEM ARE
WILLING TO DO SOME TUITION
REIMBURSEMENT BECAUSE IT IS
HARDER AND HARDER TO FIND THESE
PEOPLE
>> ALL RIGHT, KATE, THANK YOU SO
MUCH
>> THANK YOU
>>> NEXT, WE'RE "ON THE MONEY.
A HUNGRY DOG WILL EAT WHATEVER
IS IN THE BOWL
BUT IS FRESHLY MADE FOOD
HEALTHIER AND WORTH THE HIGHER
COST
ONE BUSINESS IS BETTING THE
FARM
Termites.
We're on the move.
Hey Rick, all good?
Oh yeah, we're good.
We're good.
Terminix.
Defenders of Home.
>>> DOG FOOD USED TO COME OUT OF
A CAN OR A SCOOP FROM A
TEN-POUND BAG.
TODAY, MORE PET OWNERS ARE
WATCHING WHAT'S IN THE MEALS
THEY GIVE THEIR PETS
AS SUE HERRERA FOUND, IT WAS THE
SEARCH FOR A HEALTHY FOOD FOR A
SICK DOG THAT LED TWO
ENTREPRENEURS TO SEE IF THEY
WERE BARKING UP THE RIGHT TREE
>> Reporter: FOR TWO YEARS, JADA
SUFFERED WITH STOMACH ISSUES
HER OWNER, BRET PADULSKI, TRIED
ALL KINDS OF FOODS FROM KIBBLES
TO CANS, AND FREEZE-DRIED TO
RAW.
HE WAS CONSTANTLY RUNNING HOME
TO CHECK ON JADA
>> I FELT SO BAD FOR HER
IT WAS -- IT WAS A -- LIKE A
HEARTBREAKING TIME PERIOD.
>> Reporter: IN 2014, A VET
SUGGESTED HOME COOKING
HUMAN FOOD, BEEF AND VEGETABLES.
JONATHAN REGEV, THAT'S HIS DOG
BUDDY, ROOMED WITH PADULSKY AT
THE TIME
>> I'M LIKE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HE SAID, I'M COOKING FOR JADA.
I THOUGHT HE WAS INSANE.
I HAD NEVER SEEN ANYBODY COOKING
FOR THEIR DOG BEFORE
>> IT WAS LIKE MAGIC
ALL OF HER SYMPTOMS DISAPPEARED.
>> Reporter: UNABLE TO USE A
PRODUCT USING THE USDA'S
STANDARD FOR HUMAN FOOD, THEY
KEPT COOKING AND BEGAN
RESEARCHING.
THEY FOUND STORIES LINKING
CANCERS IN PETS TO FOOD.
COMPANIES FOCUSED ON COST
EFFICIENCY AND PRODUCTS MEETING
ONLY BARE MINIMUM STANDARDS.
>> NOTHING COMMERCIAL WAS GOING
TO BE FED TO MY DOG EVER AGAIN
>> Reporter: DOGS NEED WHAT'S
KNOWN AS A COMPLETE AND BALANCED
DIET, WITH MORE VITAMINS AND
NUTRIENTS THAN THEY GET FROM
HUMAN FOOD ALONE
SO PADULSKY AND REGEV CREATED A
MIX AND TESTED SAMPLES AT A LAB
UNTIL THEY GOT THE FARMER'S DOG.
LAUNCHING IN LATE SUMMER, 2014,
IT'S FROZEN AND SHIPPED TO
ARRIVE DAYS AFTER IT'S COOKED.
>> THIS ONE'S TURKEY, BROCCOLI,
PARSNIPS, CARROTS, AND THEN THE
VITAMIN AND MINERAL MIX.
>> Reporter: IT'S HUMAN GRADE
WITH NO PRESERVATIVES, AND YES,
THEY'VE BOTH EATEN IT.
>> SOMEBODY WAS LIKE, WHEN WAS
THE LAST TIME YOU ATE IT
I WAS FEEDING JADA, AND I TOOK A
BITE
>> Reporter: DR. CARLY FOXX AT
THE ANIMAL MEDICAL CENTER IN NEW
YORK SAYS SHE USUALLY RECOMMENDS
COMMERCIALLY AVAILABLE FOOD AS
LONG AS IT'S COMPLETE AND
BALANCED
SO IS FRESHLY MADE HUMAN FOOD
BETTER
SHE SAYS MAYBE
>> IT IS BENEFICIAL FOR A PET TO
EAT HUMAN-GRADE FOOD IF IT'S
SOMETHING THAT IS AVAILABLE TO
YOU AND IT'S SOMETHING THAT
YOU'RE ABLE TO PROVIDE TO YOUR
PET.
I THINK IT'S SOMETHING THAT YOU
SHOULD ABSOLUTELY DISCUSS WITH
YOUR VETERINARIAN.
>> Reporter: COSTS DEPEND ON THE
SIZE OF A DOG, AVERAGING ABOUT
$29 A WEEK
THE FARMER'S DOG HIT THE MARKET
JUST AS AMERICAN SPENDING ON PET
FOOD BEGAN TRENDING UP, ALMOST
$30 BILLION IN 2018.
UP MORE THAN 30% IN FOUR YEARS
>> THIS IS NOT JUST A SICK DOG
THING.
THIS IS AN EVERY DOG THING
WE WANTED A COMPANY WHOSE ENTIRE
FOCUS WAS MAKING DOGS HEALTHY.
>> AND BRET AND JONATHAN SAY
THEY ARE NOW SHIPPING MORE THAN
A MILLION MEALS A MONTH.
>> WOW
>> PRETTY GOOD BUSINESS, RIGHT
>> THAT IS A BIG PICKUP.
MORE THAN I WOULD HAVE
ANTICIPATED WITH THAT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> HOW DO THEY KNOW WHAT KIND OF
FRESH FOOD TO SHIP TO YOUR DOG
>> WHAT YOU CAN DO, YOU GO ON
THEIR WEBSITE AND YOU FILL OUT A
QUESTIONNAIRE.
AND IT ASKS YOU THINGS LIKE THE
ACTIVITY LEVEL OF THE DOG, THE
BREED OF THE DOG, ANY HEALTH
CONCERNS THAT YOU HAVE WITH THE
DOG.
AND THEN THEY WILL CUSTOMIZE THE
DIET FOR YOUR PARTICULAR PET
>> I WONDER WHAT THEY'D DO FOR
120-POUND DOG, MY AGE.
PROBABLY BETTER EATING THAN I DO
FOR MYSELF
>> PEEP SPEND A LOT OF MONEY ON
PETS
REGULAR COMMERCIAL DOG FOOD
ISN'T THAT CHEAP ANYWAY.
IT'S NOT COSTING YOU ALL THAT
MUCH MORE IF -- IF AT ALL
DEPENDING ON THE BREEDS OF YOUR
DOG.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH
GREAT TO SEE YOU
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU, TOO.
>>> UP NEXT "ON THE MONEY," A
LOOK AT THE NEWS FOR THE WEEK
AHEAD.
FIRST, HOW THE STOCK MARKET
ENDED THE WEEK
>>> HERE ARE THE STORIES COMING
UP THAT MAY IMPACT YOUR MONEY
THIS WEEK.
ON MONDAY, WE'LL BE GETTING THE
CLOSELY WATCHED RETAIL SALES
NUMBERS FOR JANUARY.
ON TUESDAY, THE CONSUMER PRICE
INDEX IS RELEASED AS AN
IMPORTANT MEASURE OF INFLATION
ON WEDNESDAY, WE GET THE DURABLE
GOODS NUMBER FOR JANUARY
THOSE ARE ITEMS INTENDED TO LAST
AT LEAST THREE YEARS
THURSDAY, IT'S A REPORT ON REAL
ESTATE
NEW HOME SALES NUMBERS WILL BE
OUT.
AND FOR ALL YOU MATH NERDS, IT'S
NATIONAL PI DAY, P-I, NOT P-I-E.
3.14, GET IT, MARCH 14th, 3.14,
IF YOU LAUGHED, YOU'RE A NERD,
TOO.
>>> I'M BECKY QUICK.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR JOINING
US
NEXT WEEK, A NEW TAKE ON
FARM-TO-TABLE FOOD
WHERE YOUR SALAD IS SO LOCAL
THAT THE FRESH GREENS ARE GROWN
IN THE BASEMENT.
HMM.
>>> EACH WEEK KEEP IT RIGHT
HERE
WE'RE "ON THE MONEY.
HAVE A NICE WEEKEND.