Guys do whatever it takes to
deal with shave irritation.
So, we re-imagined the razor
with the new Gillette SkinGuar
It has a unique guard
between the blades.
That's designed to reduce
irritation during the shave.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
Gillette.
SFWLI MY THANKS TO YOU FOR
WATCHING.
THAT DOES IT FOR OUR HOUR, "MTP
DAILY" STARTS NOW.
>> IT WAS A SLOW NEWS DAY ABOUT
AN HOUR AGO, AND THEN YOU KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED?
WE GOT SOME NEWS.
IF IT IS MONDAY WE HAVE BREAKING
NEWS ABOUT IMPEACHMENT.
>> GOOD EVENING, I'M KATY TUR IN
FOR CHUCK TODD, THE PRESIDENT
REPORTEDLY TOLD VOTERS THAT THE
DEMOCRATS HATE JEWISH PEOPLE.
AND BOB MUELLER COULD BE
DELIVERING HIS REPORT TO THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT REALLY ANY
MINUTE.
BUT WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH
BREAKING NEWS BECAUSE AT A
MOMENT WHEN EVERYONE WANTS TO
KNOW IF BOB MUELLER'S REPORT
WILL INCLUDE POTENTIALLY
IMPEACHABLE OFFENSES, SPEAKER OF
THE HOUSE NANCY PELOSI BASICALLY
SAID THAT THE DEMOCRATS WILL NOT
MOVE TO IMPEACH THE KNOT MATTER
WHAT THE REPORT FINDS.
SHE SAYS I'M NOT FOR
IMPEACHMENT.
THIS IS NEWS, I'M GOING TO GIVE
YOU SOME NEWS RIGHT NOW BECAUSE
I HAVE NOT SAID THIS TO ANY
PRESS PERSON BEFORE, BUT SINCE
YOU ASKED AND I HAVE BEEN
THINKING ABOUT THIS, IMPEACHMENT
IS SO DIVISIVE, I DON'T THINK WE
SHOULD GO DOWN THAT PATH, HE IS
NOT WORTH IT.
PELOSI SAID THE PRESIDENT IS
UNFIT FOR OFFICER AND SEVEN IN
TEN DEMOCRATS THAT VOTED IN THE
MIDTERM SAID THAT CONGRESS
SHOULD IMPEACH THE PRESIDENT AND
THAT WAS BEFORE THERE WAS ANY
HARD EVIDENCE, AND NOW THE
DEMOCRATIC LEADER IS ALL BULL
RULING IT OUT.
JOINING TONIGHT'S PANEL, THE
"N YORK TIMES" POLITICAL
REPORTER AND MSNBC POLITICAL
ANALYST NICK CONFISCORY.
GARRETT, HOW IS THIS GOING TO
RESONATE ON CAPITOL HILL?
>> I THINK THERE WILL BE TWO
GROUPS HERE AMONG DEMOCRATS IN
PARTICULAR, THOSE THAT ARE
FRUSTRATED, A LOT OF THE YOUNGER
AND NEWER DEMOCRATS THAT MADE IT
CLEAR THEY WANT TO GO DOWN THE
PATH OF IMPEACHMENT.
THEY WILL BE FRUSTRATED, AND
THERE IS ANOTHER GROUP OF FOLK
THAT'S ARE FRANKLY TIRD OF
BEING ASKED THIS QUESTION.
AND I THERE ARE TWO IMPORTANT
CAVEATS.
THAT UNLESS THE EVIDENCE IS
COMPELLING AND BIPARTISAN, SHE
IS NOT WILLING TO GO DOWN THIS
PATH.
THAT REMAINS A POSSIBILITY.
SHE IS NOT SLAMMING THE DOOR
HERE ENTIRELY.
IN THE LEAD UP TO THE ANSWER SHE
SAID THIS IS NOT MAKING NEWS,
PELOSI HAS BEEN PRETTY CLEAR
FROM THE PODIUM AND OTHER AREAS
THAT SHE DOESN'T WANT TO RACE
HEADLONG INTO IMPEACHMENT.
THEY HAVE BEEN VERY DELIBERATE
ABOUT THE PACING OF THEIR
AMBITIONS.
THEY DON'T WANT TO BE SEEN AS
JUST GOING AGAINST DONALD TRUMP,
AND THE OTHER CAVEAT IS THAT HE
IS JUST NOT WORTH IT.
THERE IS SO MUCH CONFIDENCE
AMONG DEMOCRATS THAT HE CAN BE
BEATEN AT THE BALLOT BOX THAT IT
IS NOT IMPORTANT TO GALVANIZE
HIS SUPPORTERS AND RUNNING INTO
A BRICK WALL IN THE SENATE IF
THEY DON'T HAVE THE GOODS TO
HAVE CONVICTED ON THE SENATE
SIDE.
>> WHY DO IT NOW, NICK?
SHE KNEW IT WOULD MAKE NEWS.
>> EVERYONE IS WAITING FOR THE
MUELLER REPORT.
EVERYONE THINKS THERE WILL BE A
PIVOT POINT.
AND I THINK THAT IS CORRECT.
UNLESS THERE IS SOMETHING THAT
MAKE THEM, MAKE THE REPUBLICANS
WANT AN IMPEACHMENT.
>> A LOT OF COLLEAGUES SAID WE
HAVE TO WAIT UNTIL ROBERT
MUELLER COMES OUT WITH THE
REPORT, AND SHE IS ALL BUT
TAKING THAT OFF OF THE TABLE.
>> YEAH, I DON'T KNOW, THE FULL
SCOPE OF WHAT SHE IS THINKING
FOR STRATEGY.
MOST AMERICANS, 70% OF AMERICANS
SAY WE WANT SOMETHING TO BE
DONE.
THAT'S WHY WE VOTED FOR
DEMOCRATS IN 2018.
I DON'T NECESSARILY KNOW IF YOU
P
POLLED THE SAME PEOPLE, IF THEY
KNEW THAT IMPEACHMENT IS A TWO
STEP PROCESS, PERHAPS THAT
POLING WOULD HAVE BEEN
DIFFERENT.
>> YOU THINK IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
LESS FAVORABLE?
>> RIGHT, I DON'T THINK
AMERICANS REALIZE THAT
IMPEACHING HIM DOESN'T MEAN
YOU'RE REMOVING HIM FROM OFFICE.
>> BUT YOU'RE SURFACING EVIDENCE
AND YOU'RE PRESENTING A CASE
THAT IS EITHER COMPELLING ENOUGH
OR NOT.
>> THAT IS TRUE, BUT I THINK
THAT SUBSEQUENTLY WHAT THEY'RE
DOING IS IT ALMOST SERVES THE
SAME PURPOSE.
OF -- WE HAVE LEGALLY CTRUM
SIGNIFICANT INFORMATION THAT IS
NEW BASED ON REPORTING FROM LAST
WEEK THAT WE DIDN'T HAVE.
SO I THINK THAT EACH NEW PIECE
IS PUT IN THE BUCKET OF DID O
NOT REELECT THIS PERSON, AND
PERHAPS THE VOTERS WILL BE DOING
THE REMOVING.
>> IT IS CONGRESS'S RIGHT
ACCORDING TO THE CONSTITUTION TO
IMPEACH HIM FOR HIGH CRIMES AND
MISDEMEANORS.
WE HAVE FAIRLY CONCLUSIVE
EVIDENCE THAT HE COMMITTED ONE
OF THOSE CRIMES VIA MICHAEL
COHEN, THROUGH THE CAMPAIGN VIE
NANS VIOLATIONS.
FACT IS THAT IT IS STILL
EXTRAORDINARY, A BLACK MARK ON
ANY PRESIDENCY.
ANDREW JOHNSON OR BILL CLINTON.
IF THAT'S WHAT LAW REQUIRES,
THAT'S WHAT OUGHT TO BE DONE.
NANCY PELOSI IS ALSO A
CONSTITUTIONAL FIGURE.
AND SHE HAS OBLIGATIONS THAT --
>> SHE SAYS SHE BELIEVES HE
VIOLATED THE CONSTITUTION.
SHE SAID HE IS JUST NOT WORTH
IT, HERE IS THE OTHER UP WITH,
HOLD ON, I HAVE IT, ARE WE
TALKING ETHICALLY.
SHE WAS ASKED IF HE WAS FIT TO
BE PRESIDENT, ETHICALLY UNFIT,
INTELLECTUALLY UNFIT, AND --
>> YEAH, THIS IS ALL A MATTER OF
OPINION, BUT HE HAS TAKEN AN
OATH OF OFFICE AND IS HE
FULFILLING THAT OATH OF OFFICE
AND HE IS NOT.
>> BUT BY SAYING THIS, IF SHE IS
RULING OUT IMPEACHMENT, IS SHE
SAYING THE PRESIDENT IS ABOVE
THE LAW FOR THE REST OF HIS
TERM?
>> NO, I THINK SHE IS GOING TO
FOCUS ON THE ELECTIONING, AN
INSTEAD OF CALLING IT
IMPEACHMENT IT WILL GIVE HIM
AMMUNITION.
>> IS THIS BECAUSE IN 2020 THEY
WANT TO FOCUS ON IDEAS AND NOT
SUCK UP ALL OF THE OXYGEN AND
FOCUS ON IMPEACHING THE
PRESIDENT.
>> I THINK IT IS TELEVISED
HEARINGS.
IT IS WATER GATE --
>> SO ISN'T THAT GIVING HIM A
POLITICAL FOOTBALL?
>> NO, IT IS TOO, YOU CAN'T COIN
IT IN ONE WORD, RIGHT?
YOU CAN'T SAY THE DEMOCRATS ARE
TRYING TO IMPEACH ME AS OPPOSED
TO THE DEMOCRATS ARE CONDUCTING
OVERSIGHT IN A VARIETY OF AREAS.
>> BUT YOU DON'T WANT TO GIVE
HIM MORE AMMUNITION, I'M NOT
SAYING I AGREE 100% WITH THE
STRATEGY.
I HAVE GRAPPLED WITH THE THOUGHT
THAT MAYBE YOU IMPEACH HIM SET A
STANDARD, BUT I DON'T THINK IT
WILL SUCCEED BECAUSE THERE IS NO
CHANCE IN THE SENATE.
MAYBE THAT IS WHERE WE NEED TO
PUT OUR FOCUS AND MAYBE START
ASKING HARD QUESTIONS TO MITCH
McCONNELL.
>> FIST OF ALL, SHE CAN TAKE
THIS BACK WHEN EVER SHE WANTS,
SFLIEGT IF THE PROSECUTIONS COME
OUT WITH SOMETHING
EXTRAORDINARY, SHE IS CAY THAT
IS WHAT I WAS TALKING ABOUT.
SECOND WHAT IS THE MOST LIKELY
WAY FOR HER TO HOLD AN STAND
OUR -- SOME TIME IN THE FALL OF
2020?
IS IT TRYING HIS HIGH CRIMES IN
THE COURT OF PUBLIC OPINION.
AND I'M NOT SURE IT HELPS THEM
TO DO THIS.
>> I THINK THE AMERICAN PUBLIC
IS LOOKING FOR A PARTY THAT IS
NOT CYNICAL, EVEN IN THE LAW,
AND IS NOT ALWAYS OPERATING
ACCORDING TO A MEDICAL
CALCULATION.
I THINK THAT KIND OF POLITICS
THAT SAYS THE PRESIDENT VIOLATED
A LAW, THERE IS A PENALTY
MANDATED IN  CONSTITUTION, IF
IT DOESN'T PASS THE SENATE, THAT
WILL BE A SHAME ON THE
REPUBLICANS THEN.
>> IF DEMOCRATS AND PEOPLE
ACCUSE THE REPUBLICANS OF
PUTTING PARTY OVER COUNTRY BY
NOT REALLY INVESTIGATING THE
PRESIDENT, NOT ASKING HIM
QUESTIONS, AND PUTTING POLITICS
FIRST, CAN DEMOCRATS BE ACCUSED
OF THE SAME THING?
>> THEY'RE PUTTING POLITICS
FIRST BECAUSE YOU NEED TO
IMPEACH THIS PRESIDENT, YOU'RE
WORRIED ABOUT THE 2020 CHANCES.
>> DON'T SEE IT THAT WAY.
IT IS PART OF THEIR
CONSTITUTIONAL RESPONSIBILITY.
I COULD SEE A SCENARIO WHERE YOU
COULD ARGUE THAT THE EXPENSIVE
ALLEGATIONS ARE WORTH IT.
I JUST THINK THAT TO NICK'S
POINT, IT IS A CALCULATION THAT
MAY BE REQUIRED IN THIS MOMENT.
DO WE WANT TO REALLY GO THROUGH
AN IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDING WHERE
THE PRIDENT CAN WAKE UP EVERY
MORNING AND TWEET ABOUT
HARASSMENT.
>> WHAT PRECEDENT DOES THAT SET
FOR THE FUTURE.
>> THE LAST TIME WE WENT THROUGH
IT WAS OVER SOMETHING SO MINUTE.
>> EXACTLY, BUT IT IS NOT SO
MINUTE.
>> THIS ONE IS EASY TO EXPLAIN
TO THE PUBLIC.
THE PRESIDENT APPEARS TO HAVE
PAID OFF A PORN STAR AND PLAYBOY
MODEL, TO HELP HIMSELF WITH THE
2016 ELECTION AND HE GOT AWAY
WITH IT.
>> IF AMERICANS WANT TO GO DOWN
THAT RD THEY NEED TO MAKE IT
AWARE TO THE DEMOCRATS, YOU CAN
CALL NANCY PELOSI ON THE PHONE
AND SAY I DEMAND THAT DEMOCRATS
ACT ON THIS AND BEGIN
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS.
>> KRISTIN WELKER, YOU HAVE THE
REACTION FROM THE WHITE HOUSE,
WHAT ARE THEY SAYING?
>> PRETTY DEFIANT RESPONTS FROM
SARAH HUCKABEE STANDARDS, I JUST
SPOKE WITH HER AND ASKED HER TO
RESPOND.
SHE SAID LOOK IMPEACHMENT SHOULD
NEVER BE ON THE TABLE BECAUSE
THE PRESIDENT IS DOING A GREAT
JOB.
AND I PRESSED HER AND I SAID
DOES THIS LOWER YOUR LEVEL OF
CONCERN TO HEAR THE HOUSE
SPEAKER SAY THIS?
SARAH SANDERS SAID WE WITH
RESPECT THAT CONCERNED, WE'RE
FOCUSED ON DOING OUR JOBS.
SHE TOOK A CHANCE TO TAKE A
SWIPE AT PELOSI BECAUSE PELOSI
IS QUITE CRITICAL OF THE
PRESIDENT IN THAT INTERVIEW AS
WELL.
SHE SAID MOST AMERICANS AGREE
WITH PELOSI, SO NOT SURPRISINGLY
DEFIANCE FROM SARAH SANDERS, SHE
HAS BEEN AND OF COURSE WE'RE
AWAITING THAT ANY DAY NOW.
>> SHE HAS LEFT HERSELF AND OUT
AND LET'S JUST ALSO SAY THAT THE
DEMOCRATS TOOK BACK THE HOUSE IN
201.
>> AND HE DIDN'T WIN THE
MAJORITY OF VOTES IN 2016.
>> BRING ME BACK TO THE PRESS
DEBIT THAT IS BEING SET, AND IF
THEY'RE NOT WILLING TO GO DOWN
THIS PATH NOW, THEY WILL USE THE
SAME ATTACKS AND CALL IT
PRESIDENTIAL HARASSMENT.
THAT ATTACK IS THERE, IT WILL
ALREADY BE USED.
THERE IS A NUMBER OF
INVESTIGATIONS GOING ON IN
CONGRESS.
IS IT THAT MUCH WORSE.
>> THEY LAID OUT THE CASE FOR
WHY THERE IS A PRINCIPALED NEED.
BUT THE POLITICAL CASE AGAINST
IT --
>> YOU COMMIT A CRIME IN OFFICE,
SHOULDN'T THAT BE ENOUGH?
>> SURE, BUT WE'RE IN A COUNTRY
RIGHT NOW THAT IS SO POLARIZED
THAT IT IS ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE TO
PULL A CONSENSUS TO DO THIS
HIGHLY POLITICAL ACT.
AND ONE OF THE BEST THINGS FOR
PRESIDENT TRUMP RIGHT NOW IS TO
CONVINCE HIS VOTERS THAT HE IS
THE OBJECT OF SOMETHING UNFAIR
AND IT MAY BE THAT PELOSI IS CAL
-- CALCULATING THE BEST WAY --
>> GARRETT, WHAT WILL HAPPEN TO
DEMOCRATS.
>> I THINK THE EFFECT OF THIS
WILL RELIEF THAT POLITICAL BRSH
ON SOME OF THESE DEMOCRATS THAT
DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT EVERY DAY AND IT
WILL FIRE UP THOSE THAT DO, ALL
OF THIS WAS GOING TO PLAY OUT IN
A IN A WAY THAT COMES OVER THE
NEXT FEW MONTHS ANYWAY.
THERE IS ALREADY EXPANSIVE
INVESTIGATIONS.
AND IN THE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO CALL IT
IMPEACHMENT.
PELOSI LEFT HERSELF AN ENORMOUS
TRAP DOOR TO COME BACK OUT OF
THIS LATER IF THE EVIDENCE TURNS
UP COMPELLING.
>> BUT WHAT IS THE PRECEDENT
THAT YOU'RE SETTING FOR THE
FUTURE IF YOU'RE GOING TO DO
IMPEACHMENT BUT NOT CALL IT
IMPEACHMENT.
IF YOU HAVE THE HEARING AND THE
INVESTIGATIONS BUT YOU DON'T
CALL IT IMPEACHMENT.
>> IMPEACHMENT SHOULD WORK EVEN
WHEN IT IS INCONVENIENT.
AND I REMEMBER GEORGE W. BUSH
SQUEAKING INTO OFFICER IN 2,000
BY PROMISING TO RESTORE HONOR
AND INTEGRITY TO THE WHITE
HOUSE.
>> GARRETT, HAAKE, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
COMING UP THE SPEAKER OF THE
HOUSE DOES NOT SUPPORT
IMPEACHMENT UNLESS THERE IS
OVERWHELMING SUPPORT FOR IT.
DOES SHE KNOW SOMETHING ABOUT
THE MUELLER REPORT THAT WE DO
NOT.
WE'LL BE TALKING ABOUT THAT
ASPECT AND MUELLER'S END GAME
COMING UP NEXT.
AND THE LEGAL MIND THAT KNOWS
THIS STUFF BETTER THAN ANYONE
ELSE.
STAY WITH US.
TUFF BETTER THAN A
ELSE
AY WITH US
What does help for Heart Failure
look like?
It looks like George having a
busy day.
♪ THE BEAT GOES ON ♪
George has ENTRESTO,
a Heart Failure medicine that
helps his heart...
so he can keep on doing
Geowhat he loves.TO,
In the largest Heart Failure
study ever,
ENTRESTO was proven superior at
helping people stay alive
and out of the hospital.
It helps improve your heart's
ability to pump blood
to the body.
Don't take ENTRESTO if pregnant;
it can cause harm or death
to an unborn baby.
Don't take ENTRESTO with
an ACE inhibitor or aliskiren,
or if you've had angioedema
with an ACE or ARB.
The most serious side effects
are angioedema,
low blood pressure,
kidney problems,
or high blood potassium.
♪ THE BEAT GOES ON ♪
Ask your doctor about ENTRESTO
for Heart Failure.
That was great!
Entrust your heart to ENTRESTO.
HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN'T GET
HIGH SPEED INTERNET WHERE YOU
LIVE? WELL, YOU CAN WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITE INTERNET WHEREVER YOU
LIVE. HUGHESNET GEN 5 IS FAST.
YOU'LL GET 25MBPS, PLUS BUILT IN
WIFI, AND THERE'S NO HARD DATA
LIMITS. SO, WHEREVER YOU LIVE,
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
EVERYTHING YOU LOVE ONLINE.
CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, STAY
INFORMED, WATCH THE LATEST
VIDEOS, AND HELP YOUR KIDS GET
AHEAD. NO WONDER HUGHESNET IS
AMERICA'S NUMBER ONE CHOICE FOR
SATELLITE INTERNET. ACT NOW TO
SAVE $99 INSTANTLY WITH OUR
LIMITED TIME OFFER AND GET FREE
STANDARD INSTALLATION TOO. SO,
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR? GET
HUGHESNET GEN5. TO ORDER, CALL
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN. BE
SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR HOME PHONE
SERVICE, TOO. CALL THE NUMBER ON
YOUR SCREEN TODAY.
>>> NANCY PELOSI NIECE NEW
COMMENTS THAT SHE DOESN'T
SUPPORT IMPEACHMENT COMES AS
EVERYONE IS WAITING FOR ROBERT
MUELLER'S REPORT.
PERHAPS ANY MOMENT NOW, WE JUST
DON'T KNOW.
AS POLITICO REPORTS, THE WHITE
HOUSE THIS AFTERNOON LEFT THE
DOOR OPEN FOR THE PRESIDENT
GOING NUCLEAR AND PARDONING PAUL
MANAFORT, JUST TWO DAYS BEFORE
WE FIND OUT LONG MANAFORT WILL
SPEND IN PRISON.
JOINING ME NOW IS JOHN BREN NAN.
AND CHUCK ROSENBERG.
THE SAME QUESTION TO BOTH OF YOU
GENTLEMAN, IF NANCY PELOSI IS
SAYING I'M PEACHMENT IS NOT
WORTH IT, IS SHE ATTACHING DOWN
EXPECTATIONS ABOUT THE MUELLER
REPORT?
COULD SHE KNOW SOMETHING THAT WE
DON'T KNOW?
>> SHE COULD, BUT I DON'T THINK
SHE DOES, IT WAS SIR SURPRISING
SHE CAME OUT WITH THIS DAYTIME.
SHE DID LEAVE HERSELF AN OUT.
SHE SAID UNLESS IT IS
COMPELLING, I THINK WE ALREADY
HAVE TWO BOXES CHECKED.
I THINK THE BIPARTISAN BOX WILL
NOT BE CHECKED FROM HER VIEW.
AND IT IS NOT WHAT CONSTITUTION
SAYS, BUT I THINK IT IS THE
POLITICAL REALITIES OF
WASHINGTON ON THE EVE OF A
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION SHE
DOESN'T WANT TO GO THROUGH A
BRUISING FIGHT THAT WILL GET
THROUGH THE HOUSE, BUT HIS STYLE
IN THE SENATE WILL NOT BE
SOMETHING THAT WILL END GIVEN
THE REPUBLICANS DETERMINATION TO
STAY WITH THEM.
>> SO SHE IS GUESSING THAT
WHATEVER MUELLER COMES OUT WITH
IT WILL NOT BE ENOUGH TO
CONVINCE REPUBLICANS SO LET'S
MOVE ON FROM THIS?
>> YEAH, AND I THINK IT IS
BIPARTISAN, I THINK IT HAS TO BE
SOMETHING THAT WILL BE NOW HAVE
CONVINCE THE REPUBLICANS WHO
HAVE JUST STUCK WITH TRUMP, AND
SAY YES, THIS MEETING THE
STANDARD OF HIGH CRIMES AND
MISDEMEANORS AND HE NEEDS TO BE
OUSTED FROM OFFICE.
AT THIS POINT SHE IS TAMPING
DOWN EXPECTATIONS SO THE HOUSE
DEMOCRATS ARE FOCUS ON THEIR
INVESTIGATIONS.
>> I THINK JOHN IS RIGHT, NANCY
PELOSI IS A GIFTED POLL DECISION
MAKING A POLITICAL CALCULATION.
I DON'T THINK THERE IS ANY
CHANCE SHEOULD KNOW WHAT IS
INVOLVED IN MUELLER'S REPORT.
BY REGULATION, AND MUELLER IS A
REGULATION GUY, KATIE, HAS TO BE
CONFIDENTIAL WHEN HE TRANSMITS
IT TO THE ATTORNEY GENERAL.
HE HAS NOT LEAKED A THING.
HE IS RUNNING AN AIRTIGHT
INVESTIGATION, THE NOTION THAT
NANCY PELOSI KNOWS WHAT IS IN IT
IS FANSFUL TO ME.
>> WHAT WOULD EQUAL BAD FOR HIM,
EQUAL A CRIME, LIKE GETTING ON
THE PHONE T VLADIMIR PUTIN
SAYING HELP ME WITH THESE
E-MAILS SO I CAN TAKE DOWN
HILLARY CLINTON.
>> I THINK SINCE HE FACTED TO
ABNORMALLY I THINK HE CON VEBSED
A LOT OF PEOPLE IN WASHINGTON
THAT ANYTHING THAT HE DOES DOES
NOT REACH THAT BAR OF
IMPEACHMENT.
I THINK HE HAS BEEN INTENTIONAL
ABOUT THAT.
HE HAS GOT HIS BASE TO HOLD
THEIR NOSE AND ALL OF THAT THAT
IS CONSISTENT WITH THE
PRESIDENT -- I THINK THAT IS WHY
SO MANY PEOPLE ARE DETERMINED TO
STICK WITH IT.
>> HE LOWERED THE BAR AND RAISED
THE BAR AT THE SAME TIME.
ADAM SCHIFF WAS ON YESTERDAY AND
HE SOUNDED WORRIED.
HE WAS SAYING ROBERT MUELLER
SHOULD HAVE PRESIDENT TRUMP IN
FRONT OF HIM AND HI SHOULD
QUESTION HIM IN PERSON.
LET'S LISTEN.
>> I THINK ULTIMATELY IT IS A
MISTAKE.
THE BEST WAY TO GET THE TRUTH IS
TO PUT THE PRESIDENT UNDER OATH
BECAUSE HAS HE MADE CLAIM IN THE
PAST, HE FEELS ITS PERFECTLY
FINE TO LIE TO THE PUBLIC.
>> CHUCK, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> IN A TYPICAL INVESTIGATION,
KATIE, YOU SAVE THE MOST
IMPORTANT PEOPLE FOR LAST AND
YOU TALK TO EVERYBODY.
AND SO IT STRUCK ME AS ALMOST A
NECESSITY THAT BOB MUELLER AND
HIS TEAM TALK TO DONALD TRUMP
EXCEPT FOR ONE THING WE DON'T
KNOW THE FACTS.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT MUELLER
KNOWS, AND WE FRANKLY DON'T KNOW
WHETHER OR NOT THE PRESIDENT HAS
REES OR NOT AGREED TO BE
INTERVIEWED.
BY THE WAY I DON'T KNOW IF BOB
MUELLER WOULD WIN.
THE SUPREME COURT WOULD REQUIRE
A PRESIDENT TO GIVE NEW
EVIDENCE.
ASSUMING HE HAD A FIFTH
AMENDMENT PRIF LENG, BUT I
WORKED FOR BOB MUELLER AND FE HE
DOESN'T WANT TO TALK TO BOB
MUELLER I'M SURE HE HAS A GOOD
REASON FOR THAT.
>> CONSIDERING THE INVESTIGATION
AND CONSIDERING THE NOVELTY
THERE, IF THERE A REAL SWEAT FOR
OUR PRESIDENT, THEY FOUND
SOMETHING THERE, HOW LONG CAN
YOU SIT ON THAT, CURRENTLY SIT
ON THAT?
>> IT JUST DEPENDS ON THE FACTS.
IF IT IS SOMETHING FROM THE PAST
THAT HAS BEEN UNCOVERED THAT
DOES COMPROMISE THE NATIONAL
SECURITY OF THIS COUNTRY I THINK
IT IS A VALID QUESTION.
SHOULD WITH ALLOW A INDIVIDUAL
IN THE OVAL OFFICE THAT IS
COMPROMISEBLE.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW MUCOF THIS
INVESTIGATION ICE BERGE IS OUT
THERE.
I THINK HOW MUCH IS THERE AND
WHAT WILL BE DETERMINED WILL BE
DETERMINED BY WHAT WILL BE
PRESENTED TO THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL.
THERE IS NOTHING THAT REQUIRES A
PUBLIC STATEMENT TO GO OUT FROM
THE SPECIAL COUNCIL'S TEAM
SAYING WE HAVE TO DELIVER A
REPORT TO THE ATTORNEY GENERAL.
I THINK WILLIAM BARR WILL GET
THE OPPORTUNITY TO REVIEW THIS.
>> CHUCK, I BELIEVE, I THINK WE
WERE TOLD WE WOULD GET SOME
GUIDANCE FROM DOJ.
WE JUST WOULD NOT HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT WAS IN THE REPORT
IMMEDIATELY.
>> BUT I THINK JOHNSON'S
INSTINCTS ON THIS ARE RIGHT.
HERE IS WHY.
THE MUELLER REPORT IS REQUIRED
TO BE CONFIDENTIAL.
IT IS NOT IN THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL'S INTEREST TO KNOW HE
RECEIVED IT.
ONCE WE KNOW HE RECEIVED IT WE
START HAMMERING ON HIM, WHAT
WILL YOU DO, WHAT WILL YOU MAKE
PUBLIC?
AND SO THOROUGH, IT IS ENTIRELY
PLAUSIBLE, BUT IT IS PLAUSIBLE
THAT HE TRANSMITTED IT AND WHEN
HE DOES I IMAGINE THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO ANNOUNCE THAT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THAT HELPS T
ATTORNEY GENERAL THAT WOULD WANT
TO TO READ IT, REFLECT ON IT,
AND DETERMINE WHAT COULD BE
PROPERLY TRANSMITTED TO THE
CONGRESS AND MADE PUBLIC.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL'S MARCHING
ORDERS THAT GOVERNOR THIS REPORT
MUST BE BRIEF AND MUELLER'S
REPORT TO HIM MUST BE
CONFIDENTIAL.
>> WHAT IS ABOVE THE WATER RIGHT
NOW IS ALL OF THE ACTION WE'RE
GOING TO BE SEEING IN COURT THIS
WEEK FROM THE VARIOUS PEOPLE
LVED.
ONE OF THOSE IS PAUL MFRT.
THIS COULD DETERMINE HOW LONG HE
WILL END UP STAYING IN PRISON.
TODAY THE WHITE HOUSE WOULD NOT
EXPLICITLY RULE OUT THAT PAUL
MANAFORT WOULD NOT BE GIVEN A
PARDON.
>> RIGHT, PAUL MANAFORT SHOULD
NOT BE DANCING IN THE END ZONE
YET.
HE GOT A LENIENT SENTENCE.
HE IS LOOKING AT AN ADDITIONAL
TEN YEARS.
THE JUDGE THERE COULD RUN IT
CONSECUTIVELY AND HE STILL HAS
SIGNIFICANT EXPOSURE, WHETHER OR
NOT THE PRESIDENT WILL PARDON
HIM IS ANOTHER MATTER, BUT HE
SHOULD NOT BE DANCING IN THE
OCCASION YET.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY DOUBT THAT
MR. TRUMP WILL PARDON HIM AT
SOME POINT.
SO I BELIEVE THAT PAUL MANAFORT
WILL BE ABLE TO GET OUT OF THE
FEDERAL CHARGES, WHAT DOES HE
HAVE TO LOSE IF HE PARDONS HIM.
>> I THINK WHETHER OR NOT IT IS
HIM LEAVING OFFICE.
BUT HE HAS SPOKEN HIGHLY OF HIM.
HE FEELS THIS INVESTIGATION HAS
BEEN A WITCH HUNT.
SO WHY WOULD DONALD TRUMP ALLOW
HIM TO STAY IN JAIL.
>> WHAT ABOUT MIKE FLYNN?
WILL HE GET A PARDON AS WELL?
>> ANYTHING IS POSSIBLE WITH
TRUMP.
HE USES THE POWERS AS HE WANTS
TO.
IF THERE ARE STATE CHARGES,
THOSE COULD STICK, BUT FEDERAL
CHARGES I THINK DONALD TRUMP
WILL ULTIMATELY PARDON THEM.
>> THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
WE HAVE MORE ON THE NEWS OF
NANCY PELOSI.
WE HAVE A OUTSPOKEN DEMOCRATIC
WHO IS A MEMBER OF THE COMMITTEE
THAT WOULD START IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDINGS AND WE'LL GET HIS
FIRST RESPONSE TO SPEAKER
PELOSI, AHEAD.
TO SPEAKER
Other species avoid pain
actually... seek it out.
Other species do
difficult things
Because they have to.
We do difficult things.
Because we like to.
We think it's... fun.
Introducing the all-new
2019 Ford Ranger
Built for the strangest
of all creatures.
Oh, wow. You two are going to
have such a great trip.
Thanks to you, we will.
This is why Voya helps reach
today's goals...
...all while helping you to and
through retirement.
Can you help with these?
We're more of the plan, invest
and protect kind of help...
Voya. Helping you to
and through retirement.
HUMIRA patients,
you inspire us.
The way you triumph
over adversity.
And live your lives.
That's why we redesigned HUMIRA.
We wanted to make
the experience
better for you.
Now there's less
pain immediately
following injection.
We've reduced the size
of the needle
and removed the
citrate buffers.
And it has the same
effectiveness you
know and trust.
HUMIRA Citrate-free is here.
A little change can make
a big difference.
HUMIRA can lower your abilit
to fht infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections,
including tuberculosis, and
cancers, including lymphoma,
have happened, as have blood,
liver, and nervous system
problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas where certain
fungal infections are common
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if
you have an infection.
Ask your doctor
about HUMIRA
Citrate-free.
Here's to you.
AT&T provides Edge-to-Edge
Intelligence,
covering virtually every part of
your manufacturing business.
& so this won't happen.
Because you've made sure this
sensor
and this machine are integrated.
& she can talk to him, &
yes...
Atta, boy.
some people assign genders to
machines.
And you can be sure you won't
have any problems.
Except for the daily theft of
your danish.
Not cool!
AT&T provides Edge to Edge
Intelligence.
It can do so much for your
business,
the list goes on and on.
That's the power of &.
& this shipment will be
delivered...
Every year, our analysts
visit thousands of companies,
in a multitude of countries,
where we get to know the people
that drive a company's growth
and gain new perspectives.
That's why we go
beyond the numbers.
T. Rowe Price.
Invest with Confidence.
That's why we go
beyond the numbers.
Guys do whatever it takes to
deal with shave irritation.
So, we re-imagined the razor
with the new Gillette SkinGuard.
It has a unique guard
between the blades.
That's designed to reduce
irritation during the shave.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
Gillette.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "2020
VISION."
THERE IS A NEW POLL OUT OF IOWA,
BUT RESIST OBSESSING OVER THE
HORSE RACE NUMBERS.
WE ARE FOCUSING ON WHAT THE
VOTERS WANT.
>> WITH YOUR HELP, THIS CAMPAIGN
IS GOING TO TRANSFORM OUR
COUNTRY.
>> THE SMARTEST, THE HEALTHIEST,
THE FAIREST, AND THE MOST
PROSPEROUS NATION ON EARTH.
>> THIS CAMPAIGN IS NOT JUST
ABOUT WHAT IS WRONG RIGHT NOW.
IT IS ABOUT HAVING A VISION OF
WHERE WE CAN BE.
DEMOCRATS IN IOWA SAY THEY WANT
TO BE INSPIRED.
IN A NEW POLE OF LIKELY
DEMOCRATIC CAUCUS GOERS, 83% SAY
THEY WANT A CANDIDATE THAT WILL
FOCUS AN HARNESSING THE COUNTRY.
WHEN IT COMES TO THE ISSUES THAT
MATTER TWO RISE TO THE TOP.
>> HEALTH CARE, CLIMATE CHANGE.
>> 81% WAS CDIDATES TO TALK
ABOUT HEALTH CARE AND THAT
NUMBER IS 80% FOR CLIMATE
CHANGE.
JUST 22% SAY CANDIDATES SHOULD
TALK A LOT ABOUT IMPEACHMENT.
>> WE HAVE MORE "MTP DAILY" AND
A POSSIBLE 2020 CANDIDATE AHEAD
AFTER THIS BREAK.
A POSSIBLE 202
AFTER THIS BREAK
O
.
>>> WELCOME BACK, LOTS OF
BREAKING NEWS RIGHT NOW.
NANCY PELOSI BASICALLY JUST SAID
THE DEMTS WILL NOT MOVE TO
IMPEACH THE PRESIDENT, JOHN
BRENNAN TOLD ME THAT HE DOESN'T
HAVE ANY DOUBT THAT THE
PRESIDENT WILL PARDON PAUL
MANAFORT.
>> NANCY PELOSI SAYS TODAY THAT
SHE DOESN'T THINK THE PRESIDENT
IS WORTH IMPEACHING.
IT IS TOO DI VISIVE, WHAT ARE
YOUR THOUGHTS?
>> NO SOMEONE ABOVE THE LAW, IF
WE FIND HE BROKE THE LAW, WE
WON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
WE SHOULD MOVE TOWARD A
CONCLUSION.
I ALSO UNDERSTAND A SENTIMENT
THAT THIS PRESIDENT, AT LEAST HE
IS NOT WORTH TALKING ABOUT
IMPEACHMENT UNTIL WE HAVE
EVIDENCE BECAUSE THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE WANT TO TALK ABOUT
REDUCING THE COST OF
PRESCRIPTION DRUGS, GETTING
THEIR COMMUNITIES TO CONNECT,
THERE IS A LOT WE CAN DO AND WE
HAVE ALREADY DONE WITH
BACKGROUND CHECKS AND UPDATING
THE VOTING RIGHTS ACT.
I THINK WE WILL STAY FOCUSED BUT
HE IS NOT GETTING A FREE PASS.
>> WHERE IS THE BAR, SHE SAYS
IMPEACHMENT IS SO DIVISIVE THAT
UNLESS THERE IS SOMETHING
BIPARTISAN, I DON'T THINK WE
SHOULD GO DOWN THAT PATH BECAUSE
IT DIVIDES THE COUNTRY AND HE IS
JUST NOT WORTH IT.
BIPARTISAN IS AN OPERATIVE WORD
IN THAT SENTENCE.
YOU MIGHT FIND CRIMES, BUT DO
YOU THINK THERE WILL BE A
BIPARTISAN CONSENSUS TO IMPEACH
HIM?
OR IF MUELLER COMES OUT WIT
SOMETHING EGREGIOUS IN THAT
REPORT?
>> THE VOTERS WILL CONTINUE TO
THROW OUT ANYONE THAT DOESN'T
STAND UP TO HIM.
I THINK IT IS ALSO AN INDICTMENT
ON SO MANY THAT ARE SO UNWILLING
TO HOLD THIS PRESIDENT ACCOUNT
POSSIBLE.
CAN WE SAY HIS CONDUCT AFFECTS
THEY'RE EVERY DAY LIVES?
IS HE SELLING HOTEL ROOMS TO
FOREIGN NATIONALS TO BENEFIT
HIMSELF AND HIS FAMILY, IS HE
DIED TO A FOREIGN ADVERSARY.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO DO DONALD
TRUMP JUSTICE FOR TRUMP.
WE'RE GOING TO FOLLOW THE RULE
OF LAW THAT HE IS SO UNWILLING
TO FOLLOW.
>> BUT IF YOU NEED BIPARTISAN
SUPPORT, DOES THAT MEAN EVERYONE
HAS TO WAIT FOR THE ELECTION AND
LET THE VOTERS DECIDE?
>> I STILL HAVE HOPE, CALL ME
NAIVE, THAT REPUBLICANS WILL SEE
THIS CONDUCT IF IT CROSSES THE
LINE THEY WILL STEP FORWARD AND
THEY WILL DO WHAT THEY HAVE TO
DO.
MAYBE IT IS BETTER FOR THE
VOTERS TO THROW HIM OUT.
DONALD TRUMP WILL NOT BE THE
PRESIDENT IN 2021.
ASIDE FROM THE CORRUPTION WE'RE
SEEING, TOO MANY PEOPLE PROMISED
THEY WOULD DO BETTER AND INSTEAD
THEY HAVE A TOP FLOOR ECONOMY.
ALL OF THE BENEFITS HAVE STAYED
ON THE TOP FLOOR, WE CAN INDICT
>> WHAT ABOUT THE HUSH MONEY
PAYMENTS?
>>.
>> I THINK HE MAY BE GOING TO
JAIL FOR THAT.
>> BUT THAT'S NOT A CRIME THAT
WOULD MAKE YOU PUT POLITICS
SECOND AND THE CONSTITUTION
FIRST?
>>.
>> IT IS CERTAINLY A CRIME THAT
WE SHOULD PURSUE, BUT I DON'T
THINK THAT IS ALL WE HAVE AND I
THINK WE HAVE PLENTY OF OTHER
STUFF TO LOOK AT, I THINK THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE WANT US TO FOCUS
ON WHAT HE PROMISED THEM.
CONNECTING THE DISCONNECT,
MAKING SURE THE COMMUNITIES ALL
HAVE GOOD SCHOOLS, FREE FROM GUN
VIOLENCE, THAT IS WHAT WE WILL
FOCUS ON, BUT HE IS DIFFERENT
FROM WHAT HE WAS IN THE LAST FEW
YEARS.
NOW QUESTION CHECK AND PUT
BALANCES AGAINST HIM AND THAT IS
A BETTER PLACE THAN WE WERE
BEFORE.
>> ARE YOU CONCERNED ABOUT THE
PRECEDENT THAT REPUBLICANS SET
FIRST AND NOW REPUBLICANS MIGHT
BE SETTING AS WELL FOR WHAT THE
BAR IS FOR IMPEACHMENT FOR A
FUTURE PRESIDENT?
IF THIS PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
ATES,HERE IS A NUMBER OF
ALLEGATIONS OUT THERE, BUT EVEN
JUST WITH THE CAMPAIGN FINANCE
VIOLATION, IF THAT ISN'T ENOUGH,
ARE YOU CONCERNED ABOUT WHAT
THAT MEANS GOING FORWARD?
>>.
>> YEAH, I KNOW WHAT WE DO SETS
THE PRECEDENT FOR FUTURE
ADVISORS.
SO YOU CAN AT LEAST GO TO THAT
LINE.
I KNOW SPEAKER PELOSI IS
COGNIZANT OF THAT.
WHAT WE SHOULD LOOK ATRIMARILY
IS DOES HIS CONDUCT AFFECT OUR
RULE OF LAW.
DOES IT AFFECT OUR NATIONAL
SECURITY IN THAT HE IS
FINANCIALLY COMPROMISED.
THAT'S WHAT I THINK WE SHOULD
FOCUS ON THE MOST.
IF HE CROSSED THOSE LINES WE
WILL HAVE TO SUPPORT TO IMPEACH.
THERE ARE OTHER ISSUES I THINK
WE SHOULD BE FOCUSED ON AND HE
HAS A CHECK ON HIM THAT HE
DIDN'T HAVE BEFORE AND I THINK
WE CAN BREATHE A SIGH OF RELIEF.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO RUN FOR
PRESIDENT.
>> >> I'M CLOSE, I SEE SO MANY
PEOPLE WORK HARD BUT THEY SEE A
PROMISE OF AMERICA IS NOT COMING
TO THEM.
I WAS THE FIRST IN MY FAMILY TO
GO TO COLLEGE.
I SIGH IT ACROSS AMERICA THAT IS
NOT TRUE IN TOO MANY PLACES.
I THINK BEING GENERATIONAL,
BRING OPTIMISM, GO BIG AND BE
BOLD SOLUTION SO SO MANY
ISSUES --
>> SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE CLOSE TO A
YES?
>> YOU'RE GETTING ME PRETTY
CLOSE HERE, KATY, BUT I WILL
MAKE THE DECISION BY THE END OF
THE MONT
>> THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
>> MY PLEASURE.
>> COMING UP, JOHN BRENNAN JUST
TOLD ME HE THINKS THE PRESIDENT
WILL PARDON PAUL MANAFORT,
REACTION IN JUST A MOMENT, STICK
AROUND.
ORT,
REACTION IN JUST A MOMENT, STICK
AROUND
and just chow down midday?
-You mean, like, lunch?
-Come on. Voted
"Most Likely to Help People
Save $668 When They Switch."
-At this school?
-Didn't you get caught
in the laminating machine?
-Ha. [ Sighs ]
-"Box, have a great summer.
Danielle."
Ooh.
Danielle, control yourself.
I'd like to slow it down here
with a special discount
for a special girl.
Danielle, this one's for you.
with a special discount
for a special girl.
I don't know what's going on.
I've done all sorts of research,
read earnings reports,
looked at chart patterns.
I've even built my own
historic trading model.
And you're still not sure if you
want to make the trade?
Exactly.
Sounds like a case of
analysis paralysis.
Is there a cure?
TD Ameritrade's trade desk.
They can help gut check
your strategies
and answer all your
toughest questions.
Sounds perfect.
See, your stress level was here
and I got you down to here,
I've done my job.
Call for a Strategy Gut Check
with TD Ameritrade.
♪♪
>>> WELCOME BACK, SOMETHING BIG
IS BREWING IN MILWAUKEE.
DEMOCRATS HAVE CHOSEN THE CITY
AS THE SIGHT OF THE 2020
NATIONAL CONVENTION.
SORRY MIAMI BEACH AND HOUSTON.
WHY NEWS MILWAUKEE?
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY IS THE
PARTY OF WORKING PEOPLE AND
MILWAUKEE IS THE CITY OF WORKING
PEOPLE, BUT THERE IS SO MUCH
MORE TO MILWAUKEE, RIGHT?
RIGHT ALICE COOPER?
>> DO YOU COME TO MILWAUKEE
OFTEN?
>> WELL, I'M A REGULAR VISITOR
HERE, BUT MILWAUKEE CERTAINLY
HAD THEIR SHARE OF VISITORS.
THE FRENCH MISSIONARY AND
EXPLORERS WERE COMING HERE AS
EARLY AS THE 1600s TO TRADE WITH
THE NEETIVE AMERICANS.
>> ISN'T IT INDIAN NAME?
>> YES, IT IS ACTUALLY
PRONOUNCED MILWAUKEE.
MILWAUKEE
You should be mad at
non-seasoned travelers.
And they took
my toothpaste away.
And you should be mad at people
who take unnecessary risks.
How dare you, he's my
emotional support snake.
But you're not mad,
because you have E*TRADE,
whose tech helps you understand
the risk and reward potential
on an options trade
It's a paste. It's not
liquid or a gel.
and even explore what-if
scenarios.
Where's gate 87?
Don't get mad.
Get E*TRADE
and start trading today.
I switched to
Liberty Mutual
because they let me
customize my insurance,
and as a fitness junkie,
I customize everything.
Like my bike and my calves.
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance
so you only pay for
what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>>> IT IS TIME NOW FOR "THE
LID."
WE ALL WANT TO TALK ABOUT
"WAYNE'SWORLD" BUT WE'RE NOT A
AGO.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU SAW THIS.
I HOPE YOU DID.
HE SAID HE BELIEVES THAT DONALD
TRUMP WILL ABSOLUTELY PARDON
MANAFORT.
HE SAYS WHAT WOULD BE -- WHAT
WOULD BE THE NEGATIVE FOR HIM IF
HE DID?
>> I MEAN, THE WRITING IS ON THE
WALL.
HE HAS TALKED ABOUT IT.
>> WHAT DOES HE HAVE TO LOSE.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE WON'T DENY
IT.
THE ONLY QUESTION IS WHETHER IT
GETS THE PRESIDENT SOMETHING AT
THIS POINT IN THE INVESTIGATION
TO PARDON HIM.
AND I DEPENDS A LOT ON WHAT THE
PRESIDENT'S GAME THEORY OF WHAT
MUELLER SAYS AND WANTS TO DO,
AND ALREADY IS, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT IS.
>> AND IF MUELLER COMES AT HIM,
DOESN'T HAVE THE SMOKING GUN OR
HAS THE SMOKING GUN AND HE IS
NOT GETTING IMPEACHED, DOESN'T
HE FEEL BULLETPROOF?
>> I THINK HE PROBABLY FEELS
THAT WAY ALREADY.
IN TERMS I THINK OF MANAFORT,
SOMETIMES I THINK WE MISSTATE
THEIR RELATIONSHIP, BECAUSE
DONALD TRUMP IS TELLING US WELL,
HE WAS ONLY ON THE CAMPAIGN FOR
A SKOUPLE OF DAYS.
HE WAS ONLY THERE FOR 40
SOMETHING DAYS.
THEY'VE KNOWN EACH OTHER FOR
DECADES.
THE IDEA THAT PAUL MANAFORT WHO
WAS BUSINESS PARTNERS WITH ROGER
STONE DOES NOT HAVE THAT
DECADES-LONG RELATIONSHIP WITH
THE PRESIDENT IN ORDER TO SET UP
PARDON.
>> IT'S NOT A SURPRISE TO ME
THAT HE HAS A LOT OF EMPATHY FOR
MANAFORT IN WAYS THAT HE DS
NOT FOR OTHER FOLKS.
>> I THINK IT'S SIMPLER THAN
THAT.
AND AS SOMEBODY WHO COVERED THE
CAMPAIGN THAT.
>> DIDN'T GET ALONG.
THEY DIDN'T LIKE EACH OTHER.
IT WAS ACRIMONIOUS WHILE HE WAS
THERE.
I THINK IT'S --
>> DONALD TRUMP GET ALONG WITH
ALL THE PEOPLE THAT WORKED FOR
HIM?
>> NO, HE YELLED AT EVERYBODY.
BUT HE CERTAINLY GOT ALONG
BETTER WITH SOME PEOPLE THAN HE
GOT ALONG WITH MANAFORT.
>> A REPUBLICAN CAMPAIGN.
>> EXACTLY.
WHO WANTED TO BE THE T.
>> THE STEVE BANNON KIND OF, THE
CRAZY GUY STRATEGY.
>> WAS MY OPINION IS IF HE DOES
THAT, THE SIMPLER EXPLANATION IS
THAT HE PARNS MANAFORT BECAUSE
HE BELIEVES THE ENTIRE
INVESTIGATION IS BS, AND BY
PARDONING MANAFORT, HE IS
WASHING HIMSELF OF THE CRIMES AS
WELL.
HE IS CLEANSING HIMSELF.
>> THAT MIGHT BE HIS THEORY.
THAT WOULDN'T BE A CORRECT
THEORY BECAUSE PAUL MANAFORT WAS
THE MANAGER WHILE RICK GATES WAS
THE DEPUTY.
HE STAYED FOR MUCH LONGER AND
WILL SERIES COOPERATING.
SURE, HE COULD SEE IT THAT WAY.
I'M NOT SAYING THE REALITY
MATCHES WHAT DONALD TRUMPTHIN
>> NEITHER AM I.
IF HE DOES IT, THE BETTER
EXPLANATION IS IT EXONERATES ME
IF I DO THIS RATHER THAN WE'VE
HAD A LONG RELATIONSHIP BECAUSE
THE TWO MEN DIDN'T REAL LIKE
EACH OTHER THAT MUCH.
>> ALTHOUGH HID HE DID OWN AN
APARTMENT IN THE TRUMP TOWER HI,
DID.
>> IN THE ORBIT.
>> HE DEFINITELY DID.
IF HE DOES ISSUE A PARDON AND
SAY HE DOES IT SOONER THAN LATER
AND IT IS INTERESTING THE WHITE
HOUSE REFUSES TO RULE IT OUT,
POLITICALLY SPEAKING DOES THAT
HARM HIM WITH ANY VOTERS -- DO
ANY OF HIS VOTERS CARE?
AND DO YOU CARE IF HIS VOTERS
CARE?
>> BUT THE IMPORTANT THING HERE
IS IT' A WAY FOR HIM SAY THAT
ANY ANCILLARY CRIME COMING OUT
OF THE MUELLER PROBE PROVE IT'S
A WITCH HUNT BECAUSE YOU CAME
FO AND SAID YOU GOT HIM.
IT'S A POLITICAL ACT ON HIS PART
TO SAY THAT -- AND FORGET THE
LAW HERE -- WHICH SAYS YES IN
FACT YOU CAN PROSECUTE THOSE
CRIMES.
HE IS SAYING LOOK, THEY WENT TO
GET ME AND ALL THEY FOUND WAS
TAX EVASION.
AND THAT'S A WAY TO TELL
SUPPORTERS IT WAS A WITCH HUNT.
>> BUT DOES IT TELL
NONSUPPORTERS, THOSE FRINGE
SUPPORTERS THAT THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES, THIS
PRESIDENT DOESN'T BELIEVE IN THE
RULE OF LAW?
AND DOES THAT NEGATIVE REALLY
AFFECT HIM IN THE 2020 ELECTION,
OR IS THIS ALL SO SECONDARY TO
ALL OF THE OTHER ISSUES THAT ARE
OUT THERE?
>> YOU KNOW, I KNOW THAT VOTER,
ME.
>> TELL ME ABOUT IT, THEN.
>> WELL, THAT'SCT IT.
THIS SEEMS TO HAVE AN IMPACT ON
A VERY SMALL HANDFUL OF PEOPLE.
MAYBE BILL KRISTOL, A FEW OTHER
OTHERS OF MY CAMP THAT I COULD
MENTION.
IT'S A VERY SMALL DEMOGRAPHIC
SEGMENT, LET'S FACE IT, THOSE
WHO REALLY CARE.
THE FACT IS THAT PAUL MANAFORT
COULD BECOME AN AGENT OF
INFLUENCE OR A VICTIM OF
BLACKMAIL.
>> BUT YOU ALREADY WERE NOT
GOING TO VOTE FOR THE PRESIDENT.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY IT.
DOES IT INCLUDE ANYONE ELSE?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF IT INCLUDES
ANYONE ELSE.
LOOK, IT INCLUDES A VERY SMALL
SEGMENT OF PEOPLE, BUT I DON'T
THINK A PARDON FOR MAFT IS
IN ANY WAY A DECISIVE FACTOR.
THOSE ARE THOSE VOTERS WHO VOTED
FOR HIM RELUCTANTLY AND ARE
SAYING I'M JUST SO DISGUSTED BY
THE CONSTANT SORT OF VOLCANO OF
SCANDAL AND LEGALISTIC EVASION
AND A KIND OF SENSE OF
IMMORALITY AND CORRUPTION IN THE
WHITE HOUSE.
>> ERIC SWALWELL WAS JUST ON A
MOMENT AGO, AND HE WAS TRYING TO
JUSTIFY AND EXPLAIN NANCY
PELOSI'S DECISION TO COME OUT,
WITH HER FEELINGS ON
IMPEACHMENT.
HE ALSO -- IT'S NOT RULING OUT
RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT.
IF H DOES RUN FOR PRESIDENT,
DOES HE HAVE TO EXCUSE HIMSELF
FROM THE INVESTIGATION?
CAN YOU RUN FOR PRESIDENT
AGAINST THE MAN YOU ARE
INVESTIGATING?
>> I THINK SO.
I MEAN EVERYBODY RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT IS INVESTIGATING THE
PRESIDENT.
IT'S HALF THE SENATE IT SEEMS
LIKE.
LOOK, HE IS WELCOME TO GO JOIN
THE VAST TRUE -- I THINK THE
ENTIRE PARTY IS RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT WHICH IS A SIGN OF HOW
WEAK THEY THINK PRESIDENT TRUMP.
BUT YEAH, OF COURSE THEY CAN.
>> HE PRESIDENT TRUMP AS
VULNERABLE IN 2020.
>> NO.
>> AS THE DEMOCRATS THINK HE IS?
>> NO
I THINK THAT'S A HUGE MISTAKE
FOR DEMOCRATS TO IMAGINE THAT.
IT'S JUST TWO NUMBERS.
3.8%.
THAT'S THE UNEMPLOYMENT RATE, AS
LOW AS IT'S BEEN NEARLY SINCE
1969.
3.4% THAT WAS WAGE GROWTH LAST
YEAR.
AND IN MOST PRESIDENCIES, THOSE
NUMBERS WILL GET YOU RE-ELECTED.
IT'S JUST THAT WE HAVE AN
EXTRAORDINARY PRESIDENCY WITH AN
INCREDIBLY CORRUPT NARCISSIST
PRESIDENT.
BUT DEMOCRATS SHOULD NOTEPEAT
THE MISTAKE OF THINKING THEY'RE
GOING ROLL THIS GUY.
THAT WAS NOT OUR PERCEPTION IN
2016.
MAYBE THERE WAS SOMEBODY WALNG
AROUND FEELING OVERCONFIDENT.
I WAS NOT ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE
BECAUSE WE HAVE NOT ELECTED A
WOMAN PRESIDENT BEFORE IN THE
HISTORY OF THE UNITED STATES.
SO I DON'T THINK THAT DEMOCRATS
ARE WALKING INTO 2020 FEELING
LIKE WE GOT THIS IN THE BAG.
I THINK THERE WERE CERTAINLY
PEOPLE THAT STAYED HOME BECAUSE
THEY THOUGHT HILLARY HAD IT IN
THE BAG.
BUT I DON'T THINK THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY OR ANYBODY WORKING ON
THESE CAMPAIGNS IS WAKING UP
EVERY DAY THINKING OH, WE HAVE
THIS EASY BECAUSE DOND TRUMP'S
APPROVAL RATING --
>> EVERY DEMOCRAT CAMPAIGN COMS
DIRECTOR I HAVE SPOKEN WITH SAID
THEY BELIEVE DONALD TRUMP IS
VULNERABLE.
THEY BELIEVE HE ISBEATABLE, BUT
THEY ARE ALL, AND EVERY ONE OF
THEM ISSUES A CAVEAT BUT I HAVE
NO IDEA OF WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN BECAUSE OF 2016.
ZERLINA, BRETT AND NICK, SORRY.
YOU WANT TO TALK SO BADLY.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
You might take something
for your heart...
or joints.
But do you take something
for your brain.
With an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish,
Prevagen has been shown
in clinical trials
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
>> TECH: At Safelite AutoGlass,
we really pride ourselves
on making it easy
to get your windshield fixed.
With Safelite, you can see
exactly when we'll be there.
Saving you time
for what you love most.
>> KIDS: Whoa!
>> KIDS VO: ♪ Safelite repair,
Safelite replace ♪
More than half of our
community
have discovered
their Irish roots.
Which means your smiling eyes,
might be Irish too.
Order AncestryDNA,
And find the surprises
in you.
Just $59 through March 18th.
Get your kit today.
Ways to lose stubborn belly fat:
The Chili Pepper Sweat-Out.
Not cool.
Freezing away fat cells with
CoolSculpting?
Now that's coo
CoolSculpting safely freezes and
removes fat cells
with little or no downtime.
And no surgery.
Results and patient experience
may vary.
Some common side effects include
temporary numbness,
discomfort, and swelling.
Ask your doctor if CoolSculpting
is right for you.
And visit CoolSculpting.com
today
for your chance to win a free
treatment.