Because the man who gets out
in 12 1/2 years
has to be different in order
to be successful in society.
Pierce: I'm not this devil
of a person or this bad,
mean person
they point me out to be.
I care about people
tremendously,
and I'm not cold-hearted.
Narrator: Daylon Pierce's
victims are done
with giving him chances.
It's 15 years he's not
gonna have part of his life,
and 15 years to where I can
actually feel better
about the fact, like,
"Okay, this guy is now in jail.
It's so much more worth going
forward than staying quiet."
♪♪It's a d.
But Carlos Rafael,
A.K.A. "The Codfather,"
makes a killing
in commercial fishing.
His secret?
Lying and cheating.
This is his way of life,
to break the law repeatedly.
Narrator:
Rafael is salty.
Lelling: He's really
kind of a character.
He's very funny.
He's really profane.
Narrator:
And he can't stop bragging,
which makes The Codfather
easy to catch on tape.
But how will the feds respond
when they learn
The Codfather's secret sauce
includes a sheriff's deputy
smuggling cash?
Gary: You have to understand,
that's where 9/11 started --
Boston Logan Airport.
And now we're hearing about
a law-enforcement officer
circumventing security
at that same airport.
♪♪
Narrator: New Bedford,
Massachusetts,
is a small port city
that typically attracts
tourists and fishermen.
But in June 2015,
two self-described
Russian mobsters
show up in town.
They say they are looking
for a place to stash
more than $100 million in cash.
Their best bet is Carlos Rafael,
the crude boss
of the New Bedford Waterfront,
who has a fleet of 32
fishing boats worth millions.
The Russians tell Rafael
they want to buy his business,
but first they need
to see his books.
In response,
Rafael makes a joke.
[ Laughter ]
And then, he thinks again.
The Russians laugh,
but the joke is on Rafael.
They are the IRS,
and this undercover operation
is off to a good start.
♪♪
They are now confident they will
learn the secrets of the man
who has earned the nickname
"The Codfather."
♪♪
Rafael's story begins
in the Azores Islands
off the coast of Portugal,
where he is born.
In 1968, he convinces his family
to move to America.
Lelling:
He came here from Portugal
approximately at the age of 15.
He doesn't have much education.
He doesn't really know
the language.
He gets a job on the docks
in New Bedford.
And he just stays there.
Narrator:
In coming to New Bedford,
Rafael's family is following
generations
of Portuguese fishermen
who have come
to this famous port.
It was once the center
of the whaling industry,
but when whaling dies,
the money here moves
to what is called groundfish --
haddock, flounder,
and the fish that America
was founded on -- cod.
Cod was the reason a lot
of the colonists came here,
because they were so abundant.
It was literally the first
industry in the country.
Narrator: By the 1970s,
when Rafael is settling
into New Bedford,
enormous factory ships from
around the world are close by,
making off with millions
of pounds of fish each day.
Shelley: They would process fish
24 hours, 7 days a week.
Fishermen who were around
at that time
have said it looked
like Manhattan out there,
there were so many lights
of the boats parked
even just 60 or 70 miles
offshore.
Narrator:
The fleets of foreign boats
are legally
in international waters,
but the presence
of Soviet fishing boats
lurking just offshore
does not sit well
with Americans.
And so, in 1976, Congress
kicks out the foreigners
and establishes a zone
of 200 offshore miles
as exclusive
to the United States.
And then the government
offers subsidized loans
to U.S. fishermen.
Now they had to build up
the American fisheries,
'cause we were nothin',
and they just started
handing out free money.
Narrator: At the time,
Jim Kendall
is well into his career
as a scallop fisherman.
Kendall: Anybody who wanted
to build a boat
and find a small down payment
could go get it.
Narrator: And that is
when Carlos Rafael
launches his career
in the fishing industry.
For a young Azorean like Carlos,
New Bedford was
a place of opportunity,
and he certainly
took advantage of that.
Narrator: While working
as a fish cutter,
Rafael gets a loan in 1980,
and opens Carlos Seafood,
a fish-processing plant.
Soon after,
he buys his first boats,
perfectly positioning himself
to rake in big money.
Lelling:
He has his own captains
on his own boats
catching the fish.
When those fish come into port,
those boats are selling the fish
to his own business.
Narrator: And his timing
could not be better.
His introduction to being a
fishing operation in New England
was this chaos
of sort of a free-for-all.
And the message
quite literally was,
"There's a lot of fish out there
to catch, go catch 'em."
Narrator: And while Rafael
may enjoy fishing for fun,
for business, he sends his
captains out to catch the fish.
He stays on the shore.
Kendall: No, no, he was never
a true fisherman.
Carlos was a lot of things,
but that's one thing
he can't claim.
Narrator: And for many, that is
a significant distinction,
because professional fishermen
are people who routinely
head out into treacherous waters
in what is still one of
the most dangerous professions
in the country.
People who have been out at sea,
they learn humility.
You look at a big wave
or a big storm,
you understand humility.
And every fisherman I know
has that humility.
There's not an ounce of humility
in Carlos Rafael.
Narrator: Almost everyone
who meets him learns that.
As he tells
the IRS undercover agents,
he is among the smartest guys
on the docks.
And one of the most
important things Rafael knows
is that, to succeed,
he needs lots of boats.
Bigger is always better.
[ Laughter ]
Lelling: He's really
kind of a character.
He's sort of a loud,
boisterous guy.
He's very funny.
He's really profane.
He is memorable.
Narrator: As Carlos Rafael's
business grows,
it appears that his story
is a classic tale
of an immigrant achieving
the American Dream.
Here's a young man who
moved here from his homeland
at a very young age,
with little formal education,
and worked some very hard jobs
on the docks
and eventually saved money
to build up a business.
And that's laudable in
the most fundamental ways
that we Americans value.
Narrator: But Rafael's story
is more complicated.
Early on, people who do business
with him learn to be careful.
Well, if I shook hands with him,
I guess I'd count my fingers
after I got through
shaking hands with him,
based on his reputation.
Narrator: It is no secret that
Rafael will agree to pay a price
for a load of fish
at the morning auction,
but it is often not
a final price.
Kendall: The one time that
Carlos bought my trip,
I actually ended up
not selling to Carlos
because he tried
to cut the price
that he had agreed to pay,
and I refused to let him do so.
Narrator: Rafael says he is just
protecting his business.
But it's one thing
to gouge fishermen,
and another to cheat
the U.S. government.
For years, Rafael thinks
the U.S. can wait
for his tax payments.
But the IRS disagrees.
He's prosecuted for tax evasion,
by my office, in 1986.
And he was convicted
in that case.
Narrator: Rafael serves
four months in prison.
Mitchell:
Most people would respond
to an experience like that
and say, "You know what,
I'm never gonna let that
happen to me again."
But that wasn't
Carlos' reaction.
Narrator: No, it's not.
Rafael's reaction is to continue
to draw the attention
of law enforcement.
And it's not long before
a second indictment comes down.
This time, he is charged
with price fixing.
Lelling: The allegation was
he was colluding
with other commercial fishermen
in New Bedford
to set prices
on certain kinds of fish.
Narrator:
But he pulls out his charm
and, as he says,
"played the jury."
His strategy works.
The jury takes his side,
and he is acquitted.
As he walks out
of the courtroom,
he has a message
for the prosecutors.
That pretty well encapsulates
his feelings about authority.
He is not gonna be told
what to do
by anybody at any time.
He's his own person, and the
rules just weren't made for him.
Narrator:
Next on "American Greed,"
Rafael's chilling prediction.
♪♪
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now with T-mobile get the
Samsung Galaxy S10e included
With unlimited data for just $40
a month.
So, JARDIANCE asks...
When it comes to
type 2 diabetes,
are you thinking about
your heart?
Well, I'm managing my A1C,
so I should be all set.
Right.
Actually, you're still at risk
for a fatal heart attack
or stroke.
Even if I'm taking
heart medicine,
like statins or blood thinners?
Yep!
That's why I asked my doctor
what else I could do...
she told me about JARDIANCE.
That's right.
JARDIANCE significantly reduces
the risk of dying
from a cardiovascular event
for adults who have type 2
diabetes and heart disease.
that's why the American Diabetes
Association recommends
the active ingredient
in JARDIANCE.
And it lowers A1C?
Yeah- with diet and exercise.
JARDIANCE can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration.
This may cause you
to feel dizzy,
faint, or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis is a serious
side effect
that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting,
stomach pain, tiredness,
and trouble breathing.
A rare, but life-threatening,
bacterial infection
in the skin of the genital area
could also occur.
Stop taking JARDIANCE
and call your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of this bacterial infection,
ketoacidosis,
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic reaction
include rash, swelling,
and difficulty breathing
or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects
are sudden kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE
with a sulfonylurea
or insulin may cause
low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about all
the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
So, what do you think?
Now I feel I can do more
to go beyond lowering A1C.
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE
today.
So...
you're driven,
and you have a ton
of goals...
but you're stuck
in the vicious cycle
of credit card payments.
It's time to get
a personal loan from SoFi.
Borrow up to $100k to
pay off your credit cards,
and then pay us back with
one monthly payment.
And it's all with zero fees.
Get a personal loan,
and pay no fees.
( ♪♪ )
Get a personal loan,
and pay no fees.
Narrator: In 1994,
fishermen up and down
the New England Coast
receive stunning news --
The fish that have been
so plentiful
for hundreds of years
are disappearing.
Species like haddock,
flounder, and the mighty cod
are in a dangerous state
of decline.
We discovered,
"Wow, we can over-fish
just as much
as the Russians can."
And, you know,
bust followed boom.
Narrator: To give the fish
a chance to rebound,
the National Oceanic
and Atmospheric Administration,
NOAA, comes up with a
complicated set of regulations.
This a national crisis.
We are trying...
Narrator: At the time,
John Bullard
is the regional administrator
of NOAA.
And the rules are complex,
to say the least.
I mean, our rules are literally
that thick.
Woman:
So, fisherman, processors...
Narrator:
The fishermen are furious.
They see not only
their livelihood,
but an entire way of life
on the brink of extinction.
The new regulations means
you're out of business.
I'm gonna lose everything --
Everything I've worked for
for 35 years.
It's only a matter of time.
We're trying to survive here.
Bullard: Think about
what kind of a person
wants to go out
and brave the elements.
They're fiercely
independent people.
They're not the kind
of person who says,
"Oh, hey, regulate me."
I got no money!
You and everybody
talking, talking!
I see no money!
Narrator: And while fishermen
with small operations
are yelling...
[Bleep]
...Carlos Rafael knows
he will survive.
In Rafael's mind, "the weak"
are the hundreds of fishermen
who operate one or two boats --
people like Rodman Sykes.
Sykes is
a third-generation fisherman
operating near New Bedford,
in Point Judith, Rhode Island.
The only other thing
I ever wanted to do
was play second base
for the Red Sox,
and that didn't work out, so...
[ Laughs ]
So I became a fisherman.
Narrator: Sykes begins
his fishing career
at the same time
Rafael enters the industry --
in the good ol' days.
Sykes: Back then, you could do
whatever you wanted to do.
I mean, you throw the lines off
and go fishing
whenever you wanted,
catch whatever you wanted.
Narrator: But then he is faced
with regulations
that limit the horsepower
on his boat
and dictate that he use nets
with wider mesh
to decrease his catch.
It was just going from no
restrictions to that was scary.
You know, you're hauling net,
and you see
these great, big flounders
swimming on right
through the mesh,
just go, swimming away.
I said,
"We can't possibly do this."
Narrator: But the most severe
restriction for some fishermen
is a limitation on the number
of days a boat can be at sea.
Over time, as the fish
don't rebound,
the number of days
gets smaller and smaller.
Bullard: If someone says,
"I'm going to reduce the number
of days you can fish,"
that hits the family budget.
That has consequences.
That may mean
that the captain says,
"Sorry, guys,
we're not gonna be able
to provide health insurance,"
in the nation's
most dangerous job.
Narrator: And that means that
thousands of fishermen
are forced out of the business.
But Carlos Rafael is thriving.
He has added scallop boats
to his fleet,
and they more than make up
for the losses in groundfish.
He was doing quite fine
running his scallopers,
no doubt about it,
and making millions
and millions of dollars.
Narrator: And, as for all those
rules and regulations
to protect groundfish?
Easy.
It appears he simply
ignores them.
I don't think that he actively
sought to break them.
They just were
meaningless to him.
"I'm just gonna do
what I want to do,
because I want to do it."
Narrator: And, over time,
violations stack up --
exceeded haddock limit,
fished in closed area,
exceeded days at sea limit,
submitted false
daily-catch reports.
But, as he tells the IRS,
he is not intimidated
by government inspectors.
Bullard:
He's incorrigible.
This is his way of life,
to break the law repeatedly
and challenge
the federal government
to catch him
and then catch him again
and then catch him again.
Narrator: And the feds do
continue to catch him.
In 1999, there is
a third indictment for Rafael.
This time, he is caught
lying on an application
for a permit to catch squid,
saying he has a history
in the business.
Mullett: The government
followed up on that paperwork,
and they found that these people
had never purchased squid
from Carlos.
One of the businesses said,
"I wasn't even in business
at the time that he allegedly
sold me the squid."
Narrator: Rafael has
no defense this time.
He pleads guilty to five counts
of false statements,
and is sentenced to probation
and six months' house arrest.
And when the punishment ends,
it's back to business as usual.
And his fines mount --
$25,000 here, $30,000 there.
Those monetary penalties
probably would've
put the average fisherman
out of business.
Narrator: But Rafael can
afford the fines.
At the time, he says he is worth
at least $10 million.
And that is when
The Codfather is born.
Bullard: He called himself
"The Codfather."
So, he modeled himself
over a crime family.
He wasn't ashamed
of being a lawbreaker.
He bragged about it.
Narrator: And while Rafael
continually thumbs his nose
at law enforcement,
most other fishermen make
a different, painful choice.
Sykes: None of us
like the regulations,
but they're not just
for some people
and not others, you know,
and I try to go by them
as well as I know them.
Narrator: Next, Carlos Rafael
gets his big chance
to destroy his competition.
♪♪
(VO)
This is the Avery's.
This is the Avery's trying the
hottest new bistro.
Wait...and the
hottest taqueria?
And the hottest...What are
those? Oh, pierogis?
And this is the Avery's
wondering if eating out
is eating into saving for
their first home.
This is JC...
(Team Member)
Welcome to Wells Fargo,
how may I help?
(VO)
who's here to help with a free
Financial Health Conversation,
no strings attached.
This is the Avery's with the
support they needed to get
back on track. Well done guys.
(Team Member)
This is Wells Fargo.
Narrator: By 2009,
Carlos Rafael is running
one of the largest
commercial groundfish businesses
in the United States.
He proudly attributes
his success to his hard work.
At this point, he is a fixture
on the New Bedford Waterfront,
often entertaining visitors
at a Waterfront festival
with his tips on cutting
and buying fresh fish.
It appears that Rafael
is doing exceedingly well,
but many of his competitors
are struggling
to eke out a living
as the fish fail to rebound.
And a lolot of guys
didn't get through it.
I have a lot of friends that
have gone, lost their boats.
Narrator: And, as more and more
fishermen call it quits,
Rafael is there to take
their boat off their hands.
And that makes him a kind
of hero in New Bedford,
credited with keeping
a dying industry afloat.
Kendall:
He kept vessels fishing
which employed four or five
fishermen per boat,
several people on the shore.
There was a big upside to it.
Narrator: But Rafael
repeatedly makes it clear
that he doesn't care
about other fishermen.
At a meeting where a proposal to
provide emergency-relief money
to suffering fishermen
is discussed,
Rafael speaks up.
Kendall: Carlos said,
"To hell with them."
He says, "They're
just gonna spend it
on booze or drugs anyways."
I mean, that was
Carlos' opinion.
There was a young man who said
that he wanted to be able
to get into fishing,
and Carlos said, you know,
"This guy is never
gonna get into fishing.
I am gonna squash him
like a bug."
Quintessential Carlos.
"I'll squash him like a bug."
Shelley: He would get up
at the mic and say,
"I don't give a damn
about you small fishermen.
I'm gonna get it all."
I mean, it was not
a veiled state of mind.
Narrator: And then, in 2010,
a new set of rules
is put in place for groundfish
that gives him the edge
he is looking for.
For many, the days-at-sea
regulation is gone.
Now government scientists
will determine
how many fish of each species
can be caught in a year,
and each fisherman will be given
a percentage of that number --
a quota for how many they can
catch of each kind of fish.
And then the boat can pick
and choose when it goes out,
how many days it goes out
to catch its allotment
for the year.
Narrator: It's made to order
for Carlos Rafael,
because the percentage
a fisherman gets of a species,
like cod, for example,
is based on how many cod
a fisherman caught
in recent years.
Shelley: So the people who
fished the hardest
on the most-stressed fish
were given
the biggest percentage of
the future quota on that fish.
Narrator: And so, Rafael is able
to obtain around 50 permits
to catch millions
of pounds of fish.
Lelling:
These quotas, these permits,
were the lifeblood of
commercial fishing after 2010.
If you had a lot of permits,
you could do a lot of fishing,
you could make a lot of money.
If you didn't have
a lot of permits,
then you couldn't do a lot of
fishing and make a lot of money.
Narrator: It sounds simple,
but it is not when
it comes to groundfish,
and that is because
groundfish swim together.
And when the nets go down,
different species
get caught together.
Lelling: So, whatever fish
is the lowest quota,
once you caught your quota
of that fish,
you had to stop fishing.
So, if you caught all the yellow
tail you were allowed to catch,
you couldn't cast
your nets anymore
because you were gonna
pull in more yellow tail
among everything else
that you caught.
And so you had to stop
right there.
Narrator: And, inevitably,
some fishermen
do not have enough permits
to stay in business.
And, once again, Carlos Rafael
is there to buy their boats
and their permits,
ostensibly bailing them out,
but also serving
his personal ambition.
This may be Rafael's moment
to get total control.
But that does not mean he
will stop also trying to steal.
In October 2013,
one of his boats reports a catch
of 1,850 pounds of scallops.
But a check by NOAA of what is
really on board reveals
that the boat has
12,794 pounds --
over six times what he reports.
He gets caught, again,
and NOAA fines him $70,000.
Rafael can afford that fine,
and so he is willing
to take risks
that other fishermen
would not dare take.
Sykes: I'd be scared to death
that they'd...
He had a lot of permits,
so maybe he could afford
to lose one or two.
I've got one.
If I lose that,
a boat without permits --
not totally worthless,
but not worth much.
Lelling: They're trying
to follow the rules.
They're trying to eke out
a living with maybe three boats.
Here you have Carlos Rafael
with 40 boats.
He's cheating.
You know he's cheating.
And he's prospering.
You're not cheating,
and you're not prospering.
Narrator: And there seems to be
just one conclusion.
He's untouchable.
He's The Codfather.
Narrator: Next, Rafael lures in
co-conspirators.
At a time where
some of your compatriots
are starving to death,
you'll pretty much do
what the hell you're told.
♪♪
Sweat.
Dedication.
Cupcakes.
We played football together for
the Titans.
Now, we own a cupcake shop.
I love this new Surface Pro.
It's light, it's sleek, it's
fast.
Cupcakes are a great business.
As long as you don't eat the
profits!
Woman 1: I had no
symptoms of Hepatitis C.
Man 1: Mine...
...caused liver damage.
VO: EPCLUSA treats all
main types of chronic Hep C.
VO: Whatever your type,
ask your doctor if EPCLUSA
is your kind of cure.
Woman 2: I had the common type.
Man 2: Mine was rare.
VO: EPCLUSA has a 98%
overall cure rate.
Man 3: I just found out
about my hepatitis C.
Woman 3: I knew for years.
VO: EPCLUSA is only one pill,
once a day, taken with
or without food for 12 weeks.
VO: Before starting EPCLUSA,
your doctor will test if you
have had hepatitis B,
which may flare up,
and could cause serious
liver problems during
and after treatment.
VO: Tell your doctor if you
have had hepatitis B,
other liver or kidney problems,
HIV, or other
medical conditions...
VO: ...and all medicines you
take,
including herbal supplements.
VO: Taking amiodarone with
EPCLUSA
may cause a serious slowing
of your heart rate.
VO: Common side effects include
headache and tiredness.
VO: Ask your doctor today,
if EPCLUSA is your kind of cure.
Narrator:
For years, Carlos Rafael
is a thorn in the side
of law enforcement.
He has been prosecuted
three times,
with two convictions.
And he has paid hundreds
of thousands of dollars
in fines for civil violations.
You can cite him
for doing this and that,
and for him
it's like a parking ticket.
Something more was needed.
Narrator: And the chance
to do "something more"
comes in January 2015,
when IRS agents see an article
in the New Bedford paper
saying that Rafael
wants to sell his business.
He tells the reporter,
"I'm gonna cash in and screw."
So, I saw that article
and thought,
"If he wants to sell
his business,
maybe we're interested
in buying it."
Narrator: And so, IRS undercover
agents place a call to Rafael.
They just picked up the phone
and called him and said,
"We're a bunch of guys
from New York.
We're thinking about
buying your business.
Would you sit down with us?"
Narrator: Rafael takes the bait
and agrees to a meeting in June.
There are three undercover
agents working the operation.
One is playing the part
of a financial broker.
The other two are his clients,
who claim to be
Russian investors.
They meet Rafael at his office.
He wasn't anybody like
I ever met before.
Narrator: Because the agents
work undercover,
they asked that
their faces be concealed.
Alex: If you give him
an opportunity,
he'll talk about himself
constantly.
Gary: Larger than life.
Very in your face.
Lots of vulgarity, swearing,
yelling, screaming.
I didn't realize that
the "F" word could be used
in so many ways in a sentence,
to be quite frank.
Narrator: The Russians'
first question to Rafael --
What does he want
for his business?
His answer -- $175 million.
Lelling:
And they said to him, "Well,
we'd have to see your books."
So, when Carlos showed them
his legitimate books,
it did not support that price.
So they said to him,
"Why would we pay you
$175 million for this business?"
Narrator:
And to answer that question,
he needs to reveal his scheme --
how he gets around the law,
and keeps his profits high.
So that is his secret.
It's called lying.
This is what he does.
If a captain catches
3,000 pounds of cod,
which is a fish for which
Rafael has a low allotment,
he calls the cod something else,
like haddock,
a fish for which
he has a huge allotment.
It's just a simple matter
of falsifying official reports
that are sent to NOAA.
Rafael tells the boat captains
how to lie about
what they catch.
He lies about what he buys.
Lelling: So, back at NOAA,
when they compare the two,
they don't detect any fraud,
because they match.
Narrator: And so, Rafael
can catch whatever he wants
and not be limited by his quota,
what the government
allows him to catch.
When law-abiding fishermen
reach the end
of their allowable share
of the catch,
they are forced to stop fishing,
or they have the option
to buy more quota.
They gave me, I think,
6,000 pounds of winter flounder
for the whole year,
which starts May 1st.
So, I've already used that up.
So, in order
to stay in business,
I have to lease the rights
to catch more flounder
from another fisherman.
Narrator: Honest fishermen,
like Rodman Sykes,
are forced to pay for the right
to catch more fish.
Because he is lying
to the government,
Carlos Rafael does not
have that expense.
And Rafael claims his captains
profit from the scheme, as well,
because he requires them
to chip in on any quota
that he is forced to buy.
And later, when the scheme
is discovered,
some people on the waterfront
understand a captain's choice.
Kendall:
I can tell you one thing --
If you're a captain
of a fairly good vessel
that's making fairly good money
at a time where
some of your compatriots
are starving to death
or going out of business
or losing their homes,
you'll pretty much do
what the hell you're told.
And I don't want people
to think that, you know,
I approved of it,
but I think I understand it.
Narrator: By January 2016,
the IRS agents know they need
to get more proof
of Rafael's scheme.
And at their last meeting,
he provides it all.
Mullett:
He pulled out trip reports.
He pulled out bills of lading
and dealer reports --
all the documents that identify
what was being caught,
which boat was landing it,
and to whom it was being sold.
Narrator: It's as if he is
showing off a great achievement.
He is proud of his scheme.
Next on "American Greed,"
Rafael tries tax evasion again.
Gary: The bags of cash
were so heavy,
sometimes they would struggle
to actually carry them.
Narrator: Hear how Carlos Rafael
talks to his customers
at AmericanGreed.CNBC.com.
Want inside information
from the show?
Join the "Greed"
social network,
like us on "American Greed's"
Facebook page.
We'll be right back.
♪♪
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now with T-mobile get the
Samsung Galaxy S10e included
With unlimited data for just $40
a month.
So, JARDIANCE asks...
When it comes to
type 2 diabetes,
are you thinking about
your heart?
Well, I'm managing my A1C,
so I should be all set.
Right.
Actually, you're still at risk
for a fatal heart attack
or stroke.
Even if I'm taking
heart medicine,
like statins or blood thinners?
Yep!
That's why I asked my doctor
what else I could do...
she told me about JARDIANCE.
That's right.
JARDIANCE significantly reduces
the risk of dying
from a cardiovascular event
for adults who have type 2
diabetes and heart disease.
that's why the American Diabetes
Association recommends
the active ingredient
in JARDIANCE.
And it lowers A1C?
Yeah- with diet and exercise.
JARDIANCE can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration.
This may cause you
to feel dizzy,
faint, or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis is a serious
side effect
that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting,
stomach pain, tiredness,
and trouble breathing.
A rare, but life-threatening,
bacterial infection
in the skin of the genital area
could also occur.
Stop taking JARDIANCE
and call your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of this bacterial infection,
ketoacidosis,
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic reaction
include rash, swelling,
and difficulty breathing
or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects
are sudden kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE
with a sulfonylurea
or insulin may cause
low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about all
the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
So, what do you think?
Now I feel I can do more
to go beyond lowering A1C.
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE
today.
Narrator:
Anyone seeing Carlos Rafael
on the New Bedford Waterfront
would not suspect that the man
is worth millions of dollars.
He drives an old pickup truck.
His house is a modest home
in nearby Dartmouth
that he bought in 1980.
And while he typically keeps
the details of his finances
close to his chest,
in 2016, he is forced
to open his books
to two Russians who say
they want to buy his business.
Alex: He was sitting
behind a desk,
and, you know,
he reaches down in his drawer
and pulls out a piece of paper
with the cash payments.
Man: Okay.
Narrator: It is a receipt
of sorts for $600,000 --
money that he says he receives
from a wholesale fish dealer
in New York City.
The dealer is not in
on Rafael's fraud.
He simply buys his fish
from Rafael at a discount
because he pays with cash,
hand delivered to Rafael.
He would meet Carlos halfway
between New York and Boston
and give him a duffel bag
with cash in it for the fish.
The bags of cash were so heavy
that sometimes they would
struggle to actually carry them.
Narrator:
And the bags of cash
are deliberately
kept out of sight.
So, for Carlos,
those cash payments
never made it on his books.
So that became
unreported income.
Narrator: And that's
something of interest
to the IRS agents
he is talking to.
They ask, "What happens
to the cash?"
Mullett: Carlos said,
"I got it overseas."
Well, wait, wait.
If you have it overseas,
you have to fill out paperwork
and stuff, right?
There's currency reports
that you fill out at an airport
anytime you take more
than $10,000.
What do you mean,
you're bringing it
out of the country?
Narrator: Rafael says he has a
friend with special credentials.
That "agent" he is talking about
is a local
law-enforcement officer
breaking the law
and getting cash past security
at Boston's Logan Airport.
Gary: It was
a very big moment for us.
You have to understand,
that's where 9/11 started.
And now we're hearing about
a law-enforcement officer
circumventing controls and
security at that same airport.
So, we, right away, were
very alarmed, very worried.
Narrator: The officer is
Bristol County Sheriff's Deputy
Antonio Freitas.
Rafael says Freitas owes him.
Shortly after
Rafael makes that claim,
Freitas is caught smuggling cash
for his "friend" Carlos Rafael.
Mullett: So, Freitas was
ultimately indicted
for conspiracy
and bulk-cash smuggling.
So he was tried and convicted.
Narrator: He is sentenced
to a year in prison.
The IRS undercover operation
ends in January 2016.
The government feels it has
what it needs to move forward.
As the agents say goodbye
to Rafael,
he thinks he has
sold his business
to a couple of Russian mobsters.
After all, he is untouchable.
Gary: He would brag to us
over and over again
how no one was ever
gonna catch him,
and how everyone had been
trying to catch him
for years and years and years.
And, you know, he knew that
he was tricking everybody.
And, meanwhile, at that time,
he was the one getting tricked.
Narrator:
Next, the danger of goading
the federal government.
Carlos Rafael was quoted
in the press as saying,
"I'm a pirate.
It's your job to catch me."
♪♪
TO BE NOBODY BUT YOURSELF IN A
WORLD WHICH IS DOING IT'S BEST
TO MAKE YOU EVERYBODY ELSE...
♪ ♪ ♪
MEANS TO FIGHT
THE HARDEST BATTLE,
WHICH ANY HUMAN BEING
CAN FIGHT AND NEVER STOP.
DOES THIS SOUND DISMAL?
IT ISN'T.
♪ ♪ ♪
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL LIFE ON EARTH.
♪ ♪ ♪
(ATLAS)
Inferior phone detected.
(WOMAN)
What is happening?!?!
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL LIFE ON EARTH.
(ATLAS)
You need a new phone.
At Sprint, the new Samsung
Galaxy S10 series has arrived.
(WOMAN)
Wow.
(ATLAS)
And when you lease any of the
new Galaxy phones,
you get a Galaxy S10e from
Sprint to use.
(PAUL)
And Sprint's LTE Advanced
Network is built for Unlimited.
(ATLAS)
It's up to two times faster than
before.
(WOMAN)
No way.
(ATLAS)
Way. The data does not lie.
Punch it, Paul.
(AVO)
Switch to Sprint today.
Get a Samsung Galaxy S10e on us
when you lease your
next generation Galaxy phone.
For people with hearing loss,
visit Sprintrelay.com
Narrator: For years,
Carlos Rafael runs
a criminal operation,
believing he will
never be caught.
He confidently tells
the undercover agents...
Man: Yeah.
Narrator:
But on February 26, 2016,
more than a dozen
federal law-enforcement officers
surround Carlos Seafood
and move inside
to arrest Rafael.
Lelling: Carlos Rafael was
quoted in the press as saying,
"I'm a pirate.
It's your job to catch me."
I love that,
because that's perfect.
We caught him.
Narrator: After the raid
on Rafael's business,
with hundreds
of his records seized,
federal investigators
begin the work
of sorting out his lies.
Fish by fish, boat by boat,
sale by sale,
thousands of transactions.
Narrator: In the end,
the government comes up
with a figure.
In four years,
Rafael illegally caught
at least 782,000 pounds of fish.
Lelling: My first question was,
"Is that a lot of fish?"
So we asked an analyst at NOAA.
And the analyst said,
"If forests were your thing,
this would be like
burning down Vermont."
We said, "Okay,
that's a lot of fish."
Narrator: And it's important to
remember whose fish those are.
Shelley:
You know, this is really
a crime against all of us,
because these fish
didn't belong to Carlos.
He didn't spend a dime
raising them.
He didn't feed them.
He just went out and took them.
And he took them illegally.
And he took them, not just
from his fellow fishermen,
he took them from us.
Narrator: In March 2017,
faced with 15 hours
of undercover recordings
made by the IRS agents,
Rafael pleads guilty
to conspiracy,
falsifying federal records,
bulk-cash smuggling,
and tax evasion.
Through his attorney,
he declines
"American Greed's" request
to participate in this report.
At his sentencing hearing,
Rafael argues that,
in perpetrating his scheme,
he was actually trying to help
fishermen in New Bedford --
He wanted to keep them working.
He asks for 24 months
of "community confinement,"
claiming that his crime
was stupid, not greedy.
The judge disagrees, saying,
"This was not stupid.
This was corrupt."
He sentences Rafael
to 46 months in prison.
I think he was convinced to give
Carlos Rafael a high sentence
by the sheer extent
of the misconduct in this case
and the fact that
he had been prosecuted
three times in the past
for crimes related
to his fishing business.
So I think we were able
to convince the court that,
unless federal law-enforcement
was gonna be a complete joke,
it had to be the last time.
♪♪
Narrator: Rafael
is in federal prison,
but there is a worry
on New England waterfronts
that his crimes have
hurt the reputation
of all fishermen here,
who essentially operate
in an honor system.
Shelley: Carlos didn't care
about the honor system.
In fact, he used it
to his advantage,
and, really, in the process,
dishonored every other
law-abiding fisherman
out on the water.
Narrator: And those
law-abiding fishermen
believe that is unfair.
They have a message for anyone
who hears the story
of Carlos Rafael.
Sykes: I want them to know that
the vast majority of fishermen
in this port, New Bedford,
all up and down the East Coast,
are honest, hard-working guys.
Very hard-working guys.
Narrator: And while some want
to blame the system itself