REMEMBERED, THE LAST WORDS HE'S
KNOWN TO HAVE SAID WERE RECITED.
QUOTE, AT THE END, THE ONLY
THING THAT MATTERS IS HOW MUCH
WE LOVED.
MAY HE REST IN PEACE.
THAT WRAPS THINGS UP FOR US THIS
HOUR.
I'MWASHINGTON.
ALI PICKS THINGS UP.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS LAUNCHED
A NEW ATTACK ON CHINA AND
EUROPE, ACCUSING THEM OF PLAYING
A BIG CURRENCY MANIPULATION
GAME.
HE TWEETED UNITED STATES SHOULD
MATCH THE EFFORT OR CONTINUE TO
BE THE DUMMIES WHO SIT BACK AND
WATCH AS OTHER COUNTRIES
CONTINUE TO PLAY THEIR GAMES.
SUCH A MOVE, BY THE WAY, WOULD
DIRECTLY CONTRADICT U.S. POLICY
NOT TO MANIPULATE THE DOLLARS
VALUE TO GAIN TRADE ADVANTAGES.
AND THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT SAID
EARLIER THIS YEAR THAT NO
COUNTRY MEETS ITS CRITERIA OF
BEING LABELLED A CURRENCY
MANIPULATOR, ALTHOUGH IT PUT
CHINA AND EIGHT OTHER COUNTRIES
ON A WATCH LIST.
DONALD TRUMP HAS BEEN PUSHING
THIS IRFOR YEARS.
AS A CANDIDATE, HE REPEATEDLY
ACCUSED CHINA OF MANIPULATING
ITS CURRENCY AND VOWED TO FIGHT
BACK.
>> WE CAN'T LET THESE OTHER
COUNTRIES MANIPULATE THEIR
CURRENCIES.
THEY'RE DEVALUING THEIR
THEY'RE MAKING IT IMPOSSIBLE FOR
OUR COMPANIES, OUR COMPANIES
CANNOT COMPETE.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE OUR JOBS AND
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE OUR OWN
PRODUCT.
AND WE'RE GOING TO SELL THAT
PRODUCT ALSO.
AND WE'RE NOT GOING TO LET CHINA
AND ALL OF THESE COUNTRIES
CONTINUE TO DEVALUE THEIR
CURRENCY.
>> NOW, THE MARKETS DEFINITELY
SEEMED TO SHRUG OFF THE
PRESIDENT'S TWEET.
IN THE VERY SHORT PREHOLIDAY
TRADING DAY, THE MARKET IS
CLOSED.
THE DOW GAVE 139 POINTS TO CLOSE
AT A RECORD HIGH 26966.
AND THE S&P AS WELL.
NASDAQ ALSO CLOSING AT AN
ALL-TIME RECORD.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS.
WHAT IS CURRENCY MANIPULATION?
WELL, IT'S A POLICY OF WHICH THE
GOVERNMENT OR A LOCAL BANK SELLS
ITS OWN CURRENCY, REDUCING THE
DEMAND FOR ITS OWN CURRENCY.
WHEN YOU REDUCE DEMAND FOR
SOMETHING YOU DRIVE THE VALUE OF
IT DOWN.
WHEN THE CURRENCY DRIVES DOWN
THE VALUE OF ITS CURRENCY IT
MAKES ITS EXPORTS CHEAPER AND
IMPORTING MORE EXPENSIVE.
WHEN A COUNTRY BOOSTS ITS
EXPORTS THAT HELPS LOWER THE
TRADE DEFICIT SOMETHING
PRESIDENT TRUMP WANTS TO DO.
LOWERING THE VALUE OF THE U.S.
DOLLAR WOULD LIKELY BOOST
EXPORTS, WHILE THAT'S GOOD NEWS,
MANIPULATING THE DOLLAR COULD
ALSO CAUSE FOREIGN INVESTORS TO
MOVE THEIR INVESTMENTS ELSEWHERE
BECAUSE THE LOWER DOLLAR MEANS
LOWER RETURNS ON YOUR
INVESTMENTS.
IN ADDITION IT WOULD AFFECT THE
PRICE OF OIL, GOLD AND OTHER
COMMODITIES.
BOTTOM LINE IT'S A COMPLICATED
AND DIFFICULT BUSINESS TO
MANIPULATE THE VALUE OF YOUR
CURRENCY ON GLOBAL MARKETS.
I WANT TO HAVE A CLOSER LOOK
WITH A SENIOR FELLOW AT THE
CENTER OF BUDGET AND FELLOWS
PRIORITIES.
JAROD, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
I GUESS I WANT TO START BY
SAYING YOU'RE A PROGRESSIVE
ECONOMIST.
BUT THIS IS NOT A PARTISAN
ISSUE.
THERE ARE SCHOOLS EVER THOUGHT
OF LOWERING CURRENCY AND RAISING
BUT IT DOESN'T APPEAR TO BE A
DEMOCRAT OR REPUBLICAN ISSUE?
>> NO, IN FACT, PRESIDENTS OF
ALL STRIPES HAVE SAID WE SUPPORT
A STRONG DOLLAR AND IN THAT
SENSE TRUMP IS UNUSUAL.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING ELSE
THAT IS UNUSUAL, AT LEAST HALF
OF THAT TRUMP TWEET WAS
ACCURATE.
MANY OF OUR TRADING PARTNERS,
CHINA THE PAST HAVE MANAGED OR
MISALIGNED THEIR CURRENCY VALUES
PRECISELY THE WAY YOU DESCRIBED.
TO MAKE OUR EXPORTS CHEAPER AND
OURS TO THEM MORE EXPENSIVE.
AND THE RESULT IS A SIGNIFICANT
TRADE IMBALANCE WHICH WE'VE HAD
IN THIS COUNTRY FOR MANY
DECADES.
BUT THE IRONIC THING IS THAT
TRUMP'S ACTIONS HAVE ACTUALLY
MADE THIS PROBLEM WORSE.
THEY'VE STRENGTHENED THE DOLLAR.
>> SO, FIRST OF ALL, IS IT
INACHIEVABLE, WHEN DONALD TRUMP
SAYS WE SHOULD PLAY THAT GAME?
CAN YOU PLAY THAT GAME GIVEN
THAT THE ENTIRE WORLD COLLECTS
U.S. DOLLARS NOT JUST TO BUY
GOODS, BUT TO BUY OIL AND GOLD.
AND CAN THE U.S. UNLIKE ZIMBABWE
OR THAILAND OR A PLACE LIKE THAT
CAN IT ACTUALLY MANIPULATE ITS
CURRENCY DELIBERATELY?
>> THE ANSWER IS, YES, IT COULD.
BUT YOU RAISE A REALLY IMPORTANT
FUNDAMENTAL POINT.
THE U.S. DOLLAR IS THE PRIMARY
RESERVE CURRENCY OF THE WORLD.
THAT'S THE CURRENCY AS YOU JUST
SAID OTHER COUNTRIES OFTEN TRADE
IN.
ALSO, WHAT'S THE SAFEST ASSET IF
YOU WANT TO PARK YOUR MONEY
SOMEWHERE SAFE?
IT'S HERE IN THE U.S.
SO THAT MEANS FOLKS NEED DOLLARS
TO BUY OUR TREASURY SECURITIES.
BY THE WAY, WHEN I SAID TRUMP IS
PARTLY AT THE CORE OF THIS
PROBLEM, BY RUNNING THESE VERY,
VERY LARGE BUDGET DEFICITS
ESPECIALLY IN A PERIOD OF LOW
UNEMPLOYMENT, NOT ONLY IS OUR
COUNTRY GOING FASTER AND THAT
TENDS TO MAKE OUR DOLLAR
STRONGER THAN OTHER CURRENCIES,
BUT IT'S PULLING IN MORE CAPITAL
FROM ACROSS THE GLOBE, SEEKING
THESE SAFE ASSETS.
BUT BOTTOM LINE, YES, THERE ARE
THINGS WE COULD DO.
AND, FRANKLY, THINGS WE SHOULD
DO.
THE LEAST WE SHOULD DO IS
IDENTIFY THOSE WHO MANIPULATE
THEIR CURRENCIES AND AMAZINGLY,
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS
ESSENTIALLY REFUSED TO DO SO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT BEING THE
PRIMARY RESERVE CURRENCY OF THE
WORLD.
ONE OF THE REASONS THE U.S. IS
THAT THING IS BECAUSE IT'S
RELATIVELY STABLE.
IF YOU PUT YOUR MONEY INTO U.S.
DOLLARS TO BUY TREASURIES OR TO
BUY PROPERTY IN MIAMI OR
WHATEVER IT IS YOU DO WITH YOUR
MONEY, THE VALUE OF THE CURRENCY
DOESN'T TEND TO FLUCTUATE ALL
THAT MUCH.
IF WE SEND OUT A SIGNAL THAT
WE'RE LOOKING TO REDUCE THE
VALUE OF THE U.S. DOLLAR, WHAT'S
THE EFFECT OF ALL OF THE PEOPLE,
COMPANIES, SOVEREIGN FRONTS TO
INVEST IN DOLLARS BECAUSE IT'S A
SAFE CURRENCY?
>> IT'S REALLY HARD TO SAY
BECAUSE WE JUST DON'T DO THAT.
I WILL SAY, THOUGH, THAT THE
DOLLAR FLUCTUATES PRETTY
SIGNIFICANTLY.
IN FACT, ONE OF THE WAYS YOU
COULD TELL WHEN CHINA AND OTHERS
WERE PEGGING THEIR CURRENCY IS
BECAUSE THEY DIDN'T FLUCTUATE.
THEY KEPT IT AT A STRAIGHT LINE.
THE U.S. DOLLAR GOES UP AND
DOWN.
IT'S UP 7%, 10% OVER THE LAST
FEW MONTHS.
AND WE DON'T SEE DRAMATIC
CHANGES IN ANY OF THE KIND OF
TRADES YOU JUST MENTIONED.
SO, I ACTUALLY THINK THAT IT
WOULD BE WORTH OUR WHILE TO AT
LEAST EXAMINE WAYS IN WHICH WE
CAN PUSH BACK AGAINST THOSE WHO
MISALIGN THEIR CURRENCIES
BECAUSE IT DOES LEAD TO
SIGNIFICANT TRADE IMBALANCES.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE IT CLEAR,
THAT MOST OF WHAT DONALD TRUMP
HAS MADE THE PROBLEM WORSE.
>> JARED, GOOD TO SEE YOU AS
ALWAYS.
THANKS FOR TACKLING A
COMPLICATED TOPIC.
JARRED BERNSTEIN.
>>> WHILE THE PRESIDENT CREATES
THIS LATEST ISSUE OVER CURRENCY
MANIPULATION, THE ADMINISTRATION
IS GETTING LEGAL PUSHBACK FOR
HOW IT'S HANDLING THE IMMENSE
BACKLOG OF IMMIGRATION CASES IN
THE U.S. COURT SYSTEM.
A FEDERAL JUDGE REVERSED A
DIRECTIVE FROM ATTORNEY GENERAL
BILL BARR THAT ORDERED
IMMIGRATION JUDGES TO HOLD
ASYLUM-SEEKING MIGRANTS WITHOUT
BAIL.
IT KEPT MIGRANTS DETAINED
INSTEAD OF REDUCING THEM WHILE
THEIR CASES MOVED THROUGH THE
COURTS.
CREDIT SICKS SAY THE DIRECTIVE
WOULD HAVE KEPT UP TO 40,000
MIGRANTS IN CUSTODY FOR SIX
MONTHS OR MORE WITHOUT THE
GOVERNMENT HAVING TO JUSTIFY
DETENTIONS.
AS OF APRIL, THERE'S A BACKLOG
OF NEARLY 900,000 CASES PENDING
CASES OVERSEEN BY 424 JUDGES
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
THE U.S. DISTRICT JUDGE RULED
THAT THE POLICY WAS
UNCONSTITUTIONAL AND MAINTAINED
THOSE ENTERING THE UNITED STATES
ARE ENTITLED DUE PROCESS UNDER
THE FIFTH AMENDMENT.
THE COURT CONCLUDED AMONG THOSE
PROTECTIONS IS A LONGSTANDING
PROHIBITION AGAINST INDEFINITE
CIVIL DETENTION WITH NO
OPPORTUNITY TO TEST ITS
NECESSITY.
THE NINTH CIRCUIT HAS EXPRESSED
GRAVE DOUBTS THAT ANY STATUTE
THAT ALLOWS FOR ARBITRARY
PROLONGED DETENTION WITHOUT ANY
PROCESS IS CONSTITUTIONAL.
NOW, LET'S REMIND OURSELVES WHAT
THE PROBLEM IS THAT THE
GOVERNMENT IS SOLVING HERE.
BEFORE THIS CHANGE WAS MADE, THE
DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND SECURITY
SAYS 7.89% OF ASYLUM SEEKERS
FROM THE NORTHERN TRIANGLE
COUNTRIES, GUATEMALA, HONDURAS
AND EL SALVADOR WERE GRANTED
ASYLUM IN FISCAL YEAR 2017.
SO WHEN PEOPLE TELL YOU THERE'S
A CRAZY SYSTEM WHERE PEOPLE ARE
APPLYING FOR ASYLUM GETTING IT,
7.89% GET IT.
FIGURES SHOW 89% OF ASYLUM
SEEKERS DO IN FACT SHOW UP FOR
COURT DATES.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT 11% WHOSE
CASESES ARE DECIDED IN ABSENTIA.
TYPICALLY, DECIDED AGAINST THOSE
PEOPLE.
SO IT'S JUST IMPORTANT TO KEEP
TRACK OF WHAT THE SERIOUS
PROBLEM OR SO-CALLED SERIOUS
PROBLEM.
I WANT TO GET INTO THE NECESSITY
OF ALL OF THIS WITH NBC LEGAL
ANALYST DANNY CEVALLOS.
THIS IS A REMINDER THAT THE
CONSTITUTION OF UNITED STATES
MAKES NO DISTINCTION BETWEEN
CITIZENS OR NONCITIZENS IN ITS
PRESCRIPTION.
SO, IN THIS CASE, THE FIFTH
AMENDMENT CLAUSE THAT CALLS FOR
A SPEEDY TRIAL IS FOR EVERYBODY?
>> YES.
BUT THE GOVERNMENT ACTUALLY
ARGUED AGAINST WHAT YOU JUST
SAID BY ARGUING TO THE COURT
THAT THESE MIGRANTS ARE
EXCLUDABLE PERSONS.
THEY DON'T REALLY FIT WITHIN THE
GROUP OF PEOPLE PROTECTED BY THE
CONSTITUTION.
AND THE COURT SAID, THAT IS NOT
THE CASE IN THIS SITUATION.
AS A CRIMINAL DEFENSE ATTORNEY,
I HAVE TO TELL YOU WHEN YOUR
CLIENT IS HELD IN CUSTODY,
THERE'S SUCH A DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A CLIENT THAT IS HELD IN
CUSTODY AND NOT IN CUSTODY THAT
YOU CAN CONTACT, YOU CAN CALL,
YOU CAN MEET WITH THEM.
ANY LAWYER ALWAYS PROVIDES
BETTER LEGAL SERVICES AND THAT
CLIENT IS BETTER SERVED WHEN
THEY CAN FIGHT THEIR CASE ON THE
OUTSIDE AND NOT THE INSIDE.
WHAT'S DIFFERENT HERE, THESE ARE
NONCRIMINALS.
THESE ARE NONCRIMINALS BEING
DETAINED.
AND I SHOULD ADD A DECISION THAT
HAS HAD SUCH A RIPPLE EFFECT
THAT YOU JUST TALKED ABOUT.
STATISTICALLY, THIS IS CAUSING
IMMENSE BACKLOG IN THE COURTS.
THAT'S ANOTHER THING I CAN TELL
YOU FROM EXPERIENCE IS A VERY
DANGEROUS THING FOR THOSE WITH
CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHTS WHICH IS
EVERYONE WHICH IS A BACKLOG IN
THE CRIMINAL COURT.
>> THAT WOULD BE A PROBLEM IN
ANY COUNTRY BUT IT'S ACTUALLY
SOMETHING IN THE UNITED STATES
THAT IS IN OUR CONSTITUTION.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY OPEN TO
INTERPRETATION WHAT A SPEEDY
TRIAL IS.
BUT WHEN YOU HAVE 400 SOME ODD
IMMIGRATION JUDGES DEALING WITH
900,000 CASES -- AT OUR CURRENT
PACE, THAT'S DECADES.
>> I SAW IT WITH MY OWN EYES
COVERING THIS ISSUE AT THE
BORDER.
SLIGHTLY DIFFERENT BUT THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION MADE A SUMMARY
DECISION TO START PROSECUTING
MORE AND MORE OF THESE ENTRY
CASES.
AND THE BACKLOG.
THE COURTS ARE VERY SENSITIVE TO
BACKLOGS.
EVEN THE FEDERAL COURTS WHICH
MAY HAVE MORE RESOURCES CAN BE
CRIPPLED.
SO, TOO, THIS IMMIGRATION
PROCESS BY A DECISION THAT
CAUSES A BACKLOG BY HOLDING
PEOPLE LONGER THAN NECESSARY.
KEEP IN MIND, THE GOVERNMENT
ARGUED THAT, LOOK, THERE ARE
CASES THAT SAYS YOU CAN HOLD
PEOPLE UP TO SIX MONTHS.
WHAT'S WITH THE SEVEN DAYS SUCH
A FAST TIME LINE.
THE COURT SAID THAT'S NOT THE
ISSUE.
THE FUNDAMENTAL ISSUE IS WHETHER
OR NOT THESE PEOPLE WOULD BE
HELD WITHOUT ANY BAIL HEARING
WHATSOEVER.
>> THANK YOU, DANNY, DANNY
CEVALLOS IS OUR LEGAL ANALYST.
TO UNDERSCORE THIS, I TURN TO
THIS QUOTE, A TICKING TIME BOMB.
THAT'S HOW SENIOR MANAGERS AT
SEVERAL BORDER PATROL FACILITIES
AT RIO GRANDE DESCRIBED IT.
THE INSPECTOR GENERAL DETAILED
THE DIRE SITUATION.
GIVING A LOOK INSIDE.
DESPITE THE OUTRIGHT DENIALS BY
THE ADMINISTRATION, THE
SITUATION IS DIRE.
IN JUNE, THE OFFICE -- JUST BE
REMINDED THIS IS THE INSPECTOR
GENERAL FOR THE DEPARTMENT OF
HOMELAND SECURITY.
THIS ISN'T REPORTERS.
THE OFFICE VISITED TWO PORTS OF
ENTRY OBSERVING, VOTE, SERIOUS
OVERCROWDING AND PROLONGED
ATTENTION.
THEY FOUND THE BORDER PATROL WAS
HOLDING 8,000 DETAINEES.
WITH 3400 HELD LONGER THAN 72
HOURS GENERALLY PERMITTED UNDER
THE CUSTOMS AND BORDER
PROTECTIONS STANDARDS.
1500 OF THOSE DETAINED WERE HELD
FOR MORE THAN TEN DAYS.
926 CHILDREN WERE HELD.
ON TOP OF THAT, THE INSPECTOR
GENERAL FOUND THAT THE
CONDITIONS UNDER WHICH THESE
CHILDREN WERE DETAINED WERE
BELOW BORDER PATROL STANDARDS.
CHILDREN HAD NO ACCESS TO
SHOWERS DESPITE REQUIREMENTS
THAT REASONABLE EFFORTS BE MADE
TO PROVIDE SHOWERS TO CHILDREN
WHO HAVE BEEN IN DETENTION FOR
48 HOURS.
CHILDREN HAVE LIMITED ACCESS TO
A CHANGE OF CLOTHES.
AND TWO FACILITIES HAD NOT
PROVIDED THEM ANY ACCESS TO HOT
MEALS.
FOR ADULTS, THE CDP REQUIRES
THAT REASONABLE EFFORTS BE MADE
TO BE PROVIDED TO SHOWER.
SAYING MOST SINGLE ADULTS HAD
NOT HAD A SHOWER IN CBP CUSTODY
FOR AS LONG AS A MONTH.
BORDER PATROL WAS GIVING WEAPON
WET WIPES.
JOINING US NOW SOMEONE WHO HAS
BEEN UNTIL DETENTION FACILITIES
AND FAMILIAR WITH THEIR
CONDITIONS, MSNBC'S JACOB
SOBOROFF.
JACOB, YOU HAVE BEEN REPORTING
THIS FOR A LONG TIME AS YOUR
COLLEAGUES HERE ON MSNBC.
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS HAVE GONE
IN.
THE GOVERNMENT RESPONSE IS THESE
ARE INACCURATE REPORTS, THIS IS
NOT THE CASE BUT NOW WE'VE GOT
THE INSPECTOR GENERAL'S REPORT
FROM THE DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND
SECURITY WHICH DIRECTLY
CONTRADICTS WHAT THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN SAYING?
>> NOT ONLY DOES THIS INSPECTOR
GENERAL REPORT, ALI, DIRECTLY
CONTRADICT WHAT KEVIN McALEENAN
HAS BEEN SAYING, BUT JULIA
AINSLEY NOT ONLY IN THE RIO
GRANDE, BUT EL PASO SECTOR.
WE'RE SEEING IT ACROSS THE
BORDER.
AND THAT FLAZ TICKING TIME BOMB
IS ONE THAT'S GETTING
EVERYBODY'S ATTENTION.
YOU ARE HOUSING MIGRANTS WHO ARE
COMING HERE FOR HUMANITARIAN
RELIEF IN JAIL CELLS.
AND THAT IS SOMETHING THAT KEVIN
McALEENAN FRANKLY HAS SAID.
IT SHOULD NOT COME AS A SURPRISE
TO ANYONE IN THIS ADMINISTRATION
OR LAW ENFORCEMENT OR IN THE
POLITICAL BRANCH THAT THINGS ARE
AS BAD AS THEY ARE.
THIS ADMINISTRATION HAS MADE
THINGS WORSE BY EXACERBATING
CRISIS CEASE ON THE BORDER.
BY MAKING PEOPLE WAIT IN MEXICO
BY TELLING PEOPLE THERE ARE
LIMITED PORTS OF ENTRY, ONLY
ALLOWING A LIMITED NUMBER OF
PEOPLE THROUGH EVERY DAY.
YOU HAVE PEOPLE CROSSING
ILLEGALLY, THEY'RE BEING
DETAINED AS IF THEY WERE
CRIMINALS AND ALL THEY WANT IS
RELIEF.
LIKE THE RELIEF YOU WERE TALKING
ABOUT, DANNY CEVALLOS, ASYLUM
PROTECTION WHICH IS AN
INTERNATIONAL RIGHT.
>> DANNY, KEVIN McALEENAN HAS
CALLED FOR.
BUT THERE WAS A SECRET FACEBOOK
PAGE THAT SOMEBODY LEAKED
INDICATING THE CULTURE, AT LEAST
SOME OF THESE EMPLOYEES OF CBP
HAVE, BECAUSE THERE'S ABOUT
TEN,000 PEOPLE ON THIS PAGE.
>> THE CULTURE THAT YOU'RE
SEEING EMERGE THERE, ALI, IS ONE
THAT MATCHES DIRECTLY, THE
CONDITIONS THAT YOU'RE SEEING
INSIDE OF DETENTION FACILITIES.
AND WHILE WE CAN'T ASCRIBE THE
DEHUMANIZATION AND THE LANGUAGE
THAT WAS USED IN THOSE FACEBOOK
POSTS TO ALL OF THE AGENTS IN
BOATER PATROL.
IN FACT, I'VE METTLE EXCELLENT
MEN AND WOMEN WHO WORK FOR THE
BORDER PATROL.
YOU HAVE TO BE ALARMED BY WHAT
YOU ARE SEEING HERE.
THE COMBINATION OF PEOPLE BEING
HELD IN CONDITIONS LIKE THE ONES
THAT WE'RE LOOKING AT ON THE
SCREEN RIGHT NOW.
AND THE TYPES OF CONVERSATIONS
YOU ARE HEARING FROM THE --
REMEMBER, THESE ARE LAW
ENFORCEMENT AGENTS, ALLEGEDLY,
THAT ARE TALKING THIS WAY ABOUT
PEOPLE THEY ARE SUPPOSED TO BE
IN CHARGE OF AND SUPERVISING IS
INCREDIBLY CONCERNING.
SO, THE ACTING SECRETARY OF
HOMELAND SECURITY, KEVIN
McALEENAN AND THE LAUNCH
INVESTIGATION FROM THE OFFICE OF
PERSONAL RESPONSIBILITY, AND
THEY'LL LOOK INTO WHETHER OR NOT
THESE AGENTS ARE MEETING THE
STANDARDS THE DEPARTMENT.
I THINK IT'S PRETTY CLEAR TO SEE
JUST BY READING SOME OF WHAT WAS
ON FACEBOOK THAT THEY CERTAINLY
WERE NOT.
>> JACOB, THANK YOU.
>>> JOINING ME A CONGRESSWOMAN
WHO LED THEY ARE FELLOW
LAWMAKERS DURING THE TOUR OF THE
LARGEST FACILITY IN FLORIDA,
HOMESTEAD.
FREDERICA WILSON.
CONGRESSWOMAN, WHAT DID YOU SEE
WHILE YOU WERE THERE?
>> THANK YOU, ALI.
WELL, I'VE BEEN ON THIS MISSION
FOR TWO YEARS NOW TRYING TO
LOCATE THE GIRLS AND DO
OVERSIGHT OVER ADOLESCENT GIRLS.
I WENT TO BROWNSVILLE, TEXAS.
VISITED TWO FACILITIES THERE.
I'VE BEEN TO HOMESTEAD.
AND THEN I DECIDED TO INVITE MY
FELLOW COLLEAGUES TO GO WITH ME
TO HOMESTEAD JUST TO KEEP UP
WITH ADOLESCENT GIRLS WHO SHOULD
NOT BE IN JAIL.
AND THAT'S SPECIFICALLY WHAT
THEY'RE IN.
AND THEY'RE JUST CROWDING
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE, CROWDED AND
NOISY IN THIS JAIL.
THAT'S WHAT I CALL IT.
IT'S A JAIL.
AND THEY ARE IN CLASSES, BUT I
BELIEVE THEY SHOULD BE IN PUBLIC
SCHOOLS.
AND THE BATHROOMS, THE ONLY
TOILETS THEY CAN USE ARE
OUTSIDE.
AND THEIR DORMITORY IS ABOUT THE
SIZE OF A HIGH SCHOOL GYMNASIUM
WITH JUST BUNK BEDS, TWO FEET
APART.
>> WOW.
>> WHERE THESE CHILDREN HAVE TO
SLEEP.
AND WHEN THEY HAVE TO GO TO THE
BATHROOM AT NIGHT, THEY HAVE TO
GET UP AND GO OUTSIDE IN THE
DARK.
IN THE NIGHT.
TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
TO PORTABLE TOILETS.
>> CONGRESSWOMAN, THIS IS A
PRIVATELY RUN FACILITY IN WHICH
WE AS TAXPAYERS ARE PAYING THEM
A DAY RATE TO ACCOMMODATE THESE
STUDENTS.
A RATE IN SOME OF THESE CASES IS
SURPRISINGLY HIGH.
IN EXCESS OF $700 A NIGHT.
AND THEY'RE SLEEPING IN THIS
WAY, THEY'RE LIVING IN THIS WAY?
>> IT IS UNBELIEVABLE.
SOME OF THEM ARE SICK.
INFLUENZA IS ALL OVER THE PLACE.
THEY'RE SUFFERING, CRYING, THEY
WANT TO SEE THEIR PARENTS.
AND THE SAD PART ABOUT IT, THE
GIRLS THAT I FINALLY GOT TO SEE
AFTER DEMANDING AND STAYING OVER
TWO HOURS EVERY EVERYONE HAD
LEFT TO SEE THE GIRLS, I SAW
THIS ROOM FULL OF 17 YEAR OLDS.
AND THESE YOUNG PEOPLE ARE
ACTUALLY WAITING FOR THE DAY
THAT THEY TURN 18.
AND WHEN THEY TURN 18, THEY'RE
GOING TO SHACKLE THEIR WRISTS,
SHACKLE THEIR ANKLES AND TAKE
THEM TO JAIL.
THAT IS THE SADDEST THING.
>> WHAT DOES SUCCESS IN THIS
SITUATION LOOK LIKE TO YOU?
>> IT'S DIRE.
BECAUSE WHAT THEY'RE TRYING TO
DO AND WHAT THEY'RE GOING TO DO
IS EXPAND THIS FACILITY.
INSTEAD OF RELEASING THESE
CHILDREN OUT OF THIS FACILITY,
GIVING THEM A HOME TO WAIT ON
THEIR CASES.
AND SOME OF THEM HAVE PHONE
NUMBERS TATTOOED TO THEIR
WRISTS.
SOME OF THEM HAVE LITTLE NOTES
THAT THEY CAN SHOW ME OF AUNTIES
AND PEOPLE WHO ARE WAITING FOR
THEM.
THEY'RE EXPANDING THIS FACILITY.
AND TRYING TO TAKE 1,000 MORE.
THEY ALREADY HAVE IN EXCESS OF
2,000 CHILDREN.
IT IS UNBELIEVABLE.
UNBELIEVABLE.
AND THERE'S NO WAY TO KNOW
WHETHER THESE CHILDREN ARE
GETTING THE APPROPRIATE HYGIENE.
THESE LITTLE GIRLS ARE GOING
FROM GIRLHOOD TO WOMENHOOD.
I JUST DID NOT LIKE WHAT I SEE.
I'M GOING TO GO BACK AND KEEP
WATCHING THESE GIRLS.
BECAUSE IF ANYTHING, IF THEY CAN
DO ANYTHING ELSE FOR ME, IT'S
BEGIN TO RELEASE THESE GIRLS BY
THE HUNDREDS INTO THE COMMUNITY.
>> CONGRESSWOMAN, GOOD TO TALK
TO YOU.
CONGRESSWOMAN FREDERICA WILSON
OF FLORIDA.
>>> THERE ARE NO VACATION DAYS
IN THE RACE FOR THE 2020
CANDIDATES INTO THE JULY 4th
HOLIDAY.
CAMPAIGNING IN KEY STATES.
AMONG THEM, IOWA.
WE'LL TAKE YOU THERE AFTER THE
BREAK.
>>> LATER IN THE HOUSE,
FACEBOOK'S FIGHT AGAINST HATE
SPEECH.
CRITICS SAY IT ISN'T GOING WELL.
I'M GOING TO TALK TO SOMEBODY
WHO HAS MET WITH THE SOCIAL
MEDIA GIANT MORE THAN A DOZEN
TIMES.
WHAT HE SAYS THEY SHOULD BE
DOING ABOUT HATE ON THE
PLATFORM.
YOU'RE WATCHING MSNBC.
[Alarm Beeping]
(AVO)
Life doesn't give you many
second chances.
But a Subaru can.
(DAD)
You guys OK?
You alright?
Wow.
(AVO)
EyeSight with Pre-Collision
Braking.
Standard on the Subaru Ascent.
Presenting the three-row
Subaru Ascent.
Love is now bigger than ever.
When I book at Hilton.com
I get to select my room
from the floor plan...
Free Wi-Fi...
...and the Price
Match Guarantee.
So with Hilton
there is no catch.
Yeah the only catch
is I'm never leaving.
No I'm serious,
I live here now.
HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN'T GET
HIGH SPEED INTERNET WHERE YOU
LIVE? WELL YOU CAN, WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITE INTERNET WHEREVER YOU
LIVE. HUGHESNET GEN 5 IS FAST.
YOU'LL GET 25MBPS, PLUS BUILT-IN
WI-FI, AND THERE'S NO HARD DATA
LIMITS. SO, WHEREVER YOU LIVE,
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
EVERYTHING YOU LOVE ONLINE.
CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, STAY
INFORMED, WATCH THE LATEST
VIDEOS, AND HELP YOUR KIDS GET
AHEAD. NO WONDER HUGHESNET IS
AMERICA'S NUMBER ONE CHOICE FOR
SATELLITE INTERNET. ACT NOW TO
SAVE BIG WITH OUR LIMITED TIME
OFFER. GET FREE STANDARD
INSTALLATION BY CALLING RIGHT
NOW. SO, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING
FOR? GET HUGHESNET GEN5. TO
ORDER, CALL THE NUMBER ON YOUR
SCREEN. BE SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR
HOME PHONE SERVICE, TOO. CALL
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN
TODAY.
>>> THE 2020 DEMOCRATIC
CANDIDATES ARE HITTING THE ROAD
THIS WEEK TAKE NOTHING BREAK FOR
THE FOURTH OF JULY HOLIDAY.
TODAY, THEY'RE SPREAD ACROSS KEY
PRIMARY STATES OF IOWA, NEVADA
AND NEW HAMPSHIRE.
NOW, WE HAVE NEW POLLING ALL
SHOWING FORMER VICE PRESIDENT
JOE BIDEN IN THE LEAD.
SEC PLACE ALTERNATING BETWEEN
SENATOR KAMALA HARRIS AND
SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS.
LOOKING AT THE QUINNIPIAC POLL
HARRIS HAS CLOSED THE GAP UP 13
POINTS IN THE LAST THREE WEEKS.
VICE PRESIDENT BIDEN DOWN EIGHT
POINTS.
HARRIS STANDS AT 20%, BIDEN AT
22%.
SENATORS ELIZABETH WARREN AND
BERNIE SANDERS FOLLOW.
SENATOR HARRIS AND VICE
PRESIDENT BIDEN ARE AMONG THE
CANDIDATES CAMPAIGNING IN IOWA.
WHEN A "USA TODAY" POLL SHOWS
BIDEN CONTINUES TO LEAD.
JOINING ME NOW NBC'S VAUGHN
HILLYARD ON THE TRAIL.
WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE OUT THERE?
>> Reporter: YEAH, THIS IS WHAT
THE SCENES IN IOWA IN THE
SUMMERTIME BEGIN TO LOOK LIKE.
WITH KAMALA HARRIS IN THE WHITE,
IN WEST DES MOINES PICNIC.
BEFORE YOU TOSS TO ME, I SAW
SENATOR AMY KLOBUCHAR WALK IN
BETWEEN THE CANDIDATE, THEY'RE
THE TWO MAIN CANDIDATES HERE,
GOING TO ADDRESS SEVERAL HUNDRED
FOLKS HERE IN WEST DES MOINES.
AND SHE HAS A TOWN HALL LATER IN
THE DAY.
AND THAT CONVERSATION IS WHAT DO
YOU TAKE FROM A CANDIDATE FROM
THE DEBATE STAGE WHERE KAMALA
HARRIS THROUGH THE CONTRASTS
WITH JOE BIDEN.
WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE ON THE
CAMPAIGN TRAIL?
WELL, YOU CAN SAY IT'S BASICALLY
THE SECOND INNING.
WE'LL CONTINUE TO SEE WHAT THE
MESSAGE IS HERE.
THE FIRST STOP OVER THE COURSE
OF THREE DAYS, THEN NEW ORLEANS
AND SOUTH CAROLINA ON SUNDAY AND
MONDAY.
>> VAUGHAN, EARLIER WHEN I
TALKED TO YOU AND I ASKED YOU
WHAT KAMALA HARRIS IS GOING TO
DO FILL THE SPACE BETWEEN THOSE
MOMENTS THAT SHE TENDS TO HAVE
INCLUDING THE ONE ON THE DEBATE
STAGE THAT COST THE INCREASE IN
POLLING, YOU MENTIONED
CAMPAIGNING.
DOES SHE HAVE SOME SORT OF
STRATEGY, AS FAR AS YOU KNOW OF,
TO MAINTAIN THIS MOMENTUM?
BECAUSE PART OF IT IS SO MANY
MORE EYES ARE ON HER.
>> Reporter: EXACTLY, LOOK AT
THIS, IN A PLACE LIKE IOWA, IT
COMES DOWN TO THE TELEVISION
MARKET.
RIGHT HERE IN THE DES MOINES
TELEVISION MARKET.
TOMORROW, IN COUNCIL BLUFFS.
TOMORROW IN SIOUX CITY.
IT'S GETTING THE MESSAGE OUT,
ESSENTIALLY BRINGING IN LOCAL
TELEVISION CAMERAS HERE.
ENGAGING IN THAT CONVERSATION
THROUGH IT.
SHE RAISED $3 MILLION OVER THE
COURSE OF THREE DAYS AFTER THE
DEBATE.
SHE HAS 65 STAFFERS HERE ON THE
GROUND IN IOWA.
SHOULD WHILE SHE MAY TAKE A STOP
HERE IN A PLACE LIKE THIS, IT'S
THE STAFFERS, YOU CAN SEE THE
STAFFERS, ESSENTIALLY GETTING
NAMES, PHONE NUMBERS TO COMMIT
TO CAUCUS TO VOLUNTEER.
KAMALA HARRIS, ONE HUMAN BEING,
SHE CAN ONLY DO SO MUCH.
SHE'S HUMAN.
AND THEN THEY PUT OUT THAT
CONVERSATION WHERE THE KAMALA
HARRIS CAMPAIGN BELIEVES THEY
HAVE A REAL SHOT TO WIN HERE.
BARACK OBAMA WON HERE IN 2008.
SHE BELIEVES -- LASTLY, YOU JUST
HEARD THE NAME.
A LOT OF TIME AT THESE EVENTS,
ALI, IT COMES DOWN TO LOCAL
POLITICS.
THE SENATE CANDIDATE WHO WILL
LIKELY TAKE ON JONI ERNST, SHE'S
HERE AT THIS RALLY.
IT'S BEING OUT HERE TO SUPPORT
THEM WHICH AMY KLOBUCHAR AND
KAMALA HARRIS IS DOING TODAY.
>> FORMER VICE PRESIDENT JOE
BIDEN ALSO SPENDING HIS DAY IN
IOWA AFTER HIS CAMPAIGN
ANNOUNCED RAISED $21.5 MILLION
IN THE SECOND QUARTER.
JUST TO COMPARE THAT TO PETE
BUTTIGIEG, HE BROUGHT IN $24.8
MILLION, BERNIE SANDERS, $8
MILLION.
JOINING ME NOW FROM CEDAR RAPIDS
IOWA, MIKE, IT'S A GOOD F
FUND-RAISING HAUL, BUT IT'S NOT
BEEN GREAT FOR JOE BIDEN?
>> Reporter: YOU'RE RIGHT, ALI,
IT'S SOMETHING WE'VE SEEN FROM
THE BIDEN CAMPAIGN SINCE THE
START IN APRIL.
ANYTIME THEY'VE GONE THROUGH A
ROUGH PATCH, BEEN DEALING WITH
CONTROVERSY, THEY OFTEN TRY TO
PIVOT THE STORY LINE BACK TO A
POSITION OF STRENGTH.
SOMETIMES, THAT'S RETURNING THE
DISCUSSION FROM DEBATE BETWEEN
JOE BIDEN AND PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THAT'S, OF COURSE, THE BIG
ELECTABILITY ARGUMENT THAT'S THE
CORNERSTONE OF BIDEN'S SUPPORT
IN THE POLLS.
TODAY AS EVERYONE IS GETTING
READY TO HEAD OUT TO THE HOLIDAY
WEEKEND AND THEY'RE DEALING WITH
THAT FALLOUT, WE SAW THE BIDEN
CAMPAIGN TAKE THAT OPPORTUNITY
TO PUT OUT THAT FUNDRAISING
NUMBER, $21 MILLION.
IT'S NOT AS HIGH AS PETE
BUTTIGIEG.
BUT THE BIDEN CAMPAIGN POINTING
OUT THEY HADN'T BEEN IN THE RACE
FOR THAT FULL 90-DAY PERIOD.
IF YOU AVERAGE IT OUT, PER DAY,
HE DID IN FACT RAISE MORE MONEY
THAN ANY CONTENDERS AT LEAST
FROM WHO WE'VE HEARD SO FAR.
90% OF DONATIONS COME FROM SMALL
DONORS FROM GRASSROOTS
SUPPORTERS IN LESS THAN $200
INCREMENTS.
AND THEY'RE HIGH-DOLLAR
FUNDRAISING AS WELL.
WHAT'S IMPORTANT TO KNOW AND THE
BIDEN CAMPAIGN ALSO WANTS TO
POINT OUT A DOLLAR FOR JOE BIDEN
LOW IT'S A LOT LONGER THAN A
DOLLAR FOR EVEN KAMALA HARRIS.
WE TALK ABOUT IT A LOT ON OUR
AIR BUT MAYBE THE AVERAGE VOTER
DOESN'T HAVE A LOT OF
RECOGNITION IN.
BIDEN IS PUTTING THAT MONEY INTO
INVESTMENTS IN THE GROUND GAME.
THEY HAVE 50 PAID STAFF HERE IN
IOWA.
THEY DOUBLED THAT IN NEW
HAMPSHIRE.
YES, HE'LL SPEND THAT IN TV ADS
DOWN THE ROAD BUT INFRASTRUCTURE
AND ADS FOR TV JUST SO VOTERS
GET TO KNOW HIM.
>> THANK YOU, MIKE.
>>> THE GERMAN GOVERNMENT FINED
FACEBOOK OVER $2 MILLION OR
UNDERREPORTING HATE SPEECH ON
ITS PLATFORM.
THERE WERE MORE COMMENTS ABOUT
ANTI-SEMITIC CONTENT THAN
FACEBOOK LET ON.
IT'S SMALL, GIMP THE COMPANY'S
SIZE, IT DRAWS ATTENTION,
HOWEVER, TO THE EMBATTLED SOCIAL
MEDIA FLASH B CLASHES TO OTHER
WORLD POWERS AS HATE SPEECH
EMERGES.
THIS IS A TOPIC OF DEBATE WITH
GOVERNMENTS THROUGHOUT THE
WORLD.
JOINING ME NOW, THE PRESIDENT OF
COLOR OF CHANGE WHICH IS THE
NATION'S LARGEST ONLINE RACIAL
JUSTICE ORGANIZATION.
AND HE'S MET WITH FACEBOOK'S
CHIEF OFFICER SHERYL SANDBERG A
DOZEN TIME.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> GOOD TO BE HERE.
>> THERE'S A CONTEXT,
PARTICULARLY IN GERMAN, AS A
RESULT OF THE HOLOCAUST, THEY'RE
HYPER SENSITIVE TOWARDS THE HATE
SPEECH AND THE DEGREE TO WHICH
IT CAN CATCH ON.
IT DOES SEEM THAT THE EUROPEANS
ARE FURTHER AHEAD THAN AMERICANS
IN DEALING WITH THIS ISSUE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THE FINE IS SMALL, AS YOU SAID.
BUT THE SYMBOL OF THE FINE, THE
SYMBOL OF HOLDING AN INSTITUTION
LIKE FACEBOOK ACCOUNTABLE IS
SERIOUS.
AND UNFORTUNATELY, WE'VE NOT HAD
THAT LEVEL OF OVERSIGHT FROM THE
FTC HERE, FROM CONGRESS, FROM
THE AUTHORITIES THAT ARE
SUPPOSED TO BE STEPPING IN WHEN
INSTITUTIONS, COMMUNICATIONS
PLATFORMS OTHERS DO NOT.
>> WHY DO YOU THINK THAT IS?
IS IT A WILL THING?
IS IT AN UNDERSTANDING?
>> IT'S A COUPLE THINGS.
FIRST OF ALL, IT'S A WILL THING.
IT'S A WILL THING WHEN IT COMES
TO CONGRESS.
IT'S BECOME POLITICIZED ON BOTH
SIDES.
AND I DON'T WANT TO CREATE FALSE
EEI DIDN'T FEEL.
BUT THE FTV WINS SETTLEMENTS OR
GET FINES AND NOT ABLE TO
IMPLEMENT OR HOLD ACCOUNTABLE,
ONCE FACEBOOK GOES BACK AND
VIOLATES SOME OF THE THINGS THAT
THEY WERE CALLED OUT ON THE
FIRST PLACE.
>> YOU HAVE HAD CONVERSATIONS
WITH SHERYL SANDBERG, IN FACT,
HE'S HAD SOMETHING TO SAY ABOUT
THE CENSUS COMING OUT.
YOU CAN IMAGINE PEOPLE PUTTING
FALSE NEWS OUT ABOUT THE CENSUS
AND THAT MESSING UP THE COUNT?
>> YES, YOU CANNOT FILL OUT YOUR
CENSUS ON FACEBOOK.
TO THAT POINT, YOU KNOW, THIS
WAS PART OF LONG-TERM WORK WE'VE
BEEN DOING AT COLOR OF CHANGE.
FOR THE LAST SEVERAL YEARS,
WE'VE BEEN PURCHASING THE
ORGANIZATION TO GET REALLY CLEAR
ABOUT THEIR CIVIL RIGHTS WORK.
AND BACK IN NOVEMBER, THEY GOT
THEM TO COMMIT TO PUBLICLY
RELEASING THEIR SILL RIG CIVIL
AUDIT.
THEY DID THE FIRST PHASE IN
NOVEMBER WHICH WAS WEAK.
THIS LAST PHASE THAT THEY
RELEASED ON SUNDAY SHOWED MORE
PROGRESS.
SINCE SHERYL SANDBERG HAS TAKEN
OVER THE AUDIT AND PUT IT IN HER
OFFICE.
WE HAVE SEEN A MARKET CHANGE IN
HER COMMITMENT TO ACTUALLY
TRYING TO SOLVE THE PROBLEMS.
FOR US, METRIC OF SUCCESS IS A
DIFFERENT PROBLEM.
WE WANT THEM TO DEAL WITH HOW DO
THEY TREAT THE CENSUS LIKE THE
ELECTION.
AS A BIG EVENT WHERE ALL FORCES
COME IN BECAUSE THERE'S A LOT
THAT INFLUENCES IT.
USE RACIAL APPEALS, USE OTHER
THINGS TO SUPPRESS TURNOUTS TO
SUPPRESS PARTICIPATION.
SO, PART OF THIS IS THAT
FACEBOOK MAKES A LOT OF MONEY.
IT'S THE LARGEST COMMUNICATIONS
PLATFORM IN THE WORLD.
AND THEY HAVE A RESPONSIBILITY
TO MAKE SURE THAT THE TECHNOLOGY
THAT MOVES US INTO THE FUTURE
DOESN'T DRAG US INTO THE PAST.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO, LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS
INVESTIGATION THAT'S BEEN
ORDERED BY THE HEAD OF THE
DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND SECURITY
INTO THE SECRET FACEBOOK POSTS
THAT HAD ALMOST 10,000 PEOPLE ON
IN WHICH THEY WERE SAYING
REMARKABLY SEXIST, MISOGYNIST
RACIST THINGS ABOUT MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS AND MIGRANTS.
LOOK, IT'S 10,000 PEOPLE.
WE DON'T MEAN THAT TO TAINT THE
GOOD WORK OF THOSE IN CUSTOMS
AND BORDER PATROL NOT INVOLVED.
TALK ABOUT THIS THIS IS A SECRET
GROUP.
WE ONLY FOUND OUT ABOUT IT
BECAUSE SOMEBODY IN IT LEAKED
THE INFORMATION BECAUSE THEY
THOUGHT IT HAD GONE TOO FAR.
DOES FACEBOOK HAVE A ROLE IN
THAT?
>> YEAH, FACEBOOK, THESE PRIVATE
GROUPS THEY MINE THE DATA, AND
THEY MINE THE DATA AND THEY WORK
TO MAKE MONEY OFF OF THAT DATA.
SO THEY'VE CREATED THESE PRIVATE
GROUPS.
AND THEN THEY HAVE COMMUNITY
STANDARDS ABOUT HATE.
ABOUT WHAT YOU CAN SAY AND WHAT
YOU CAN DO ON THEIR PLATFORM.
>> AND THAT APPLIES?
>> IT SHOULD, IT DOES APPLY, AND
IT NEEDS TO APPLY, NO MATTER HOW
POWERFUL THE PEOPLE WHO ARE
DOING IT ARE.
THE TRICK IS, IT'S OKAY TO HAVE
TRAFFIC RULES, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> BUT THE TRAFFIC RULES ONLY
MATTER IF THEY APPLY TO ALL OF
US.
AND THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS
THESE PRIVATE GROUPS CAN'T EXIST
ON THEIR PLATFORM AND ALLOW FOR
THE SOWING OF HATE.
AND FACEBOOK HAS A ROLE IN THIS.
I ALSO THINK THE GOVERNMENT HAS
A ROLE.
THE FACT THAT PEOPLE FELT SO
COMFORTABLE.
IN A SPACE --
>> LAW ENFORCEMENT --
>> LAW ENFORCEMENT FIGURES THAT
GET A GUN AND BADGE AND ARE
SUPPOSED TO UPHOLD THE LAWS OF
THIS COUNTRY FELT SO COMFORTABLE
TO SAY SUCH HATEFUL AND
DEROGATORY THINKS ABOUT PEOPLE
IN PERIL AND ELECTED PEOPLE OF
COLOR AND WOMEN -- 10,000 IN THE
GROUP.
>> DID FACEBOOK MAKE THEM SAY
THESE THINGS?
PEOPLE HAD RACIST, MISOGYNIST
THINGS TO SAY.
DO WE WIN IF WE GET IT OFF OF
FAB?
>> NO, BUT I THINK WE HAVE TO
RECOGNIZE THE WAY TECHNOLOGY AND
NEW TOOLS ALLOW FOR INFORMATION
TO MOVE QUICKER, RIGHT?
IT'S LIKE LIGHTING A MATCH IS
ONE THING.
LIGHTING A MATCH NEXT TO LIGHTER
FLUID IS A DIFFERENT THING.
IN MANY WAYS, WHETHER IT'S
YOUTUBE, FACEBOOK OR TWITTER,
THESE PLATFORMS CAN BE THE
LIGHTER FLUID.
THAT MEANS WE HAVE TO KEEP AN
EYE ON IT.
AND WE HAVE TO PAY SPECIAL
ATTENTION TO HOW THIS
INFORMATION CAN SPREAD IN
DIFFERENT WAYS.
YEAH, SOMEONE CAN SAY HATEFUL
THINGS OUT ON THE STREET.
AND THAT'S FREEDOM OF SPEECH AND
THEY, YOU KNOW, NOT WITHOUT
CONSEQUENCES THEIR JOB OR
WORKPLACE OR WHATEVER.
>> RIGHT, RIGHT.
>> BUT IT'S FREEDOM OF SPEECH.
IT'S DIFFERENT WHEN YOU GO INTO
A GROUP.
YOU ARE A LAW ENFORCEMENT
FIGURE, YOU DON'T KNOW THE OTHER
10,000 PEOPLE IN THAT GROUP.
AND YOU FEEL SO COMFORTABLE
SAYING THESE THING AND DOING
THESE THINGS, YES, THERE HAS TO
BE ACCOUNTABILITY.
THERE'S ACCOUNTABILITY FOR ALL
OF US, RIGHT?
IN THE WORKPLACE.
>> IF I WAS ON A GROUP LIKE
THAT, I'D PROBABLY GET HIRED.
>> YOU'D GET FIRED.
THE PROBLEM IS, WHY SHOULD WE
EXPECT LESS FROM LAW
ENFORCEMENT?
WHY SHOULD WE LET THEM OFF THE
HOOK?
ESPECIALLY WHEN WE SEE THE
IMAGES, HORRIFIC IMAGES, COMING
FROM THE BORDER RIGHT NOW.
WE WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT THE
VERY BEST PEOPLE ARE ENGAGED IN
THIS EFFORT.
AND THAT'S NOT WHAT'S HAPPENING.
AND THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS,
ONCE AGAIN, THE TECHNOLOGY THAT
HAS SO MUCH POTENTIAL, TO BRING
US TOGETHER, SHOULD NOT DRAG US
BACK.
>> RASHAD, GOOD TO HAVE YOU
HERE.
PRESIDENT OF COLOR OF CHANGE.
>>> STILL AHEAD, DEMOCRATIC
VOTERS THINK IT'S A GREAT IDEA,
MEDICARE FOR ALL.
NEW POLLING SHOWS A LOT OF
SUPPORT FOR THE PLAN WITHIN THE
PARTY.
WHILE SOME OF THE DEMOCRATIC
CANDIDATES ARE ALREADY
CAMPAIGNING HARD ON THE ISSUE.
OTHERS SEEM TO BE WAITING FOR
THE GENERAL ELECTION BEFORE THEY
PUSH HARD ON HEALTH CARE.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK ABOUT THE
SPLIT STRATEGY AFTER THE BREAK.
YOU ARE WATCHING MSNBC.
when you can stay home
with Neulasta® Onpro®?
Strong chemo can put you
at risk of serious infection.
In a key study
Neulasta® reduced the risk
of infection from 17% to 1%
a 94% decrease.
Neulasta® Onpro®
is designed to
deliver Neulasta®
the day after chemo
and is used by
most patients today.
Neulasta® is for certain
cancer patients receiving
strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta®
if you're allergic to it
or Neupogen (filgrastim).
An incomplete dose could
increase infection risk.
Ruptured spleen,
sometimes fatal as well
as serious lung problems
allergic reactions,
kidney injuries
and capillary leak
syndrome have occurred.
Report abdominal or shoulder
tip pain, trouble breathing or
allergic reactions to
your doctor right away.
In patients with
sickle cell disorders,
serious, sometimes
fatal crises can occur.
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
If you'd rather be home
ask your doctor about
Neulasta® Onpro®.
Pay no more than $5 per
dose with Copay Card.
I had a few good tricks to help
hide my bladder leak pad.
Like the old "tunic tug".
But Always Discreet
is less bulky.
And it really
protects.
'Cause it turns liquid to gel.
So I have nothing to hide.
Always Discreet.
(ANNOUNCER)
IMPORTANT MESSAGE FOR WOMEN
AND MEN AGES 50 TO 85.
RIGHT NOW, IN AREAS LIKE YOURS,
PEOPLE HAVE ALREADY CALLED
ABOUT LIFE INSURANCE
THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM
AND RECEIVED THEIR FREE
BENEFICIARY PLANNER.
HAVE YOU RECEIVED
YOUR FREE PLANNER?
IF NOT, I ENCOURAGE YOU
TO PICK UP THE PHONE
AND TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THIS FREE OFFER.
IN ADDITION TO YOUR
FRENEFICIARY PLANNER,
YOU'LL ALSO RECEIVE
FREE INFORMATION
ON AFFORDABLE
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE
THAT HAS A LIFETIME RATE LOCK
THAT GUARANTEES
YOUR RATE CAN NEVER INCREASE
FOR ANY REASON.
IF YOU DID NOT RECEIVE
YOUR FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
CALL THIS NUMBER NOW.
PLEASE STAND BY TO LEARN MORE.
I'M ALEX TREBEK,
HERE TO TELL YOU ABOUT
A POPULAR LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
WITH A RATE LOCK
THAT LOCKS IN YOUR RATE FOR LIFE
SO IT CAN NEVER INCREASE.
DID YOU GET YOUR FREE
INFORMATION KIT?
IF NOT, PLEASE CALL
THIS NUMBER NOW.
THIS AFFORDABLE PLAN THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM
HAS COVERAGE OPTIONS
FOR JUST $9.95 A MONTH.
YOUR RATE IS LOCKED IN
AND CAN NEVER GO UP,
AND YOUR ACCEPTANCE
IS GUARANTEED
WITH NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
SEE HOW MUCH COVERAGE YOU CAN
GET FOR JUST $9.95 A MONTH.
CALL NOW FOR
YOUR FREE INFORMATION KIT.
>>> THE 20 DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES ON THE
DEBATE STAGE IN MIAMI LAST WEEK
TOUCHED ON A NUMBER OF MAJOR
ISSUES, AMONG HEM, ECONOMY,
IMMIGRATION, HEALTH CARE AND
CLIMATE CHANGE.
BUT THOSE, DO THEY MATTER TO THE
VOTERS WHO ARE GOING TO DECIDE
WHO IS GOING TO GET A CHANCE TO
TAKE ON PRESIDENT TRUMP NEXT
YEAR?
A NEW "WASHINGTON POST"/ABC NEWS
POLL FINDS 89% OF THOSE SURVEYED
SAYS HEALTH CARE IS THE TOP
ISSUE IN THE 2020 ELECTION JUST
AS IT WAS IN THE 2018 ELECTION.
GUN VIOLENCE WAS NEXT, FOLLOWED
BY WOMEN'S ISSUES.
IF THERE'S ANYBODY IN THE
AUDIENCE WHO CAN READ WHAT THOSE
THINGS SAY, I CAN'T TELL.
THERE WE GO, IMMIGRATION.
WOMEN'S ISSUES, IMMIGRATION, 80%
AT GLOBAL WARMING.
THEN THE ECONOMY.
FOREIGN POLICY, ABORTION AND
TAXES AS OF THE LEAST CONCERN TO
DEMOCRATIC LEANING VOTERS.
JOINING ME NOW, DAN BALL,
"WASHINGTON POST" CHIEF
CORRESPONDENT.
DAN, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
>> MY PLEASURE, ALI.
>> DAN, THE BIG ISSUE HERE IS
HEALTH CARE AND HOW BIG A DEAL
IT IS FOR DEMOCRATIC LEANING
VOTERS AND HOW MANY SUPPORT
MEDICARE WITH SOME PROPOSAL OF
IT.
THE MORNING COUNCIL POLL FOR
MEDICARE FOR ALL SHOWS OF ALL
VOTERS A SMALL MAJORITY SUPPORT
A MEDICARE FOR ALL.
53%.
77% OF DEMOCRATS DO.
HALF 6 INDEPENDENTS DO.
27% OF REPUBLICANS DO.
IT DOES SEEM SUPPORT FOR
MEDICARE FOR ALL OR SOMETHING
LIKE IT IS A WINNING STRATEGY
FOR DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES.
>> WELL, I THINK THERE'S THREE
QUESTIONS.
ONE IS, WHERE DO PEOPLE STAND ON
MEDICARE OR ALL OF OUR
GOVERNMENT-RUN SINGLE PAYOR
SYSTEM.
THAT'S THE FIRST QUESTION.
THE SECOND IS IF YOU'RE IN FAVOR
OF MEDICARE FOR ALL,
GOVERNMENT-RUN SYSTEM, WOULD YOU
BE IN FAVOR OF THAT IF YOU KNEW
THAT PRIVATE INSURANCE WAS GOING
TO GO AWAY.
WHAT WE FOUND IN OUR POLL,
THERE'S OVERWHELMING SUPPORT
AMONG THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY,
SELF-IDENTIFIED DEMOCRATS AND
DEMOCRATIC LEANING INDEPENDENTS
FOR A MEDICARE FOR ALL KIND OF
PROGRAM.
AND TWO-THIRDS OF DEMOCRATS SAY
THEY WOULD BE IN SUPPORT OF THAT
EVEN IF IT MEANT THE END OF
PRIVATE INSURANCE.
AMONG THE HARD CORE OF THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY, OR AMONG THE
BROAD SCALE OF THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY, THERE'S QUITE A SUPPORT
FOR IT.
WE KNOW AMONG THE CANDIDATES,
VICE PRESIDENT BIDEN IS IN ONE
PLACE.
HE'S RESISTANT TO GO THAT FAR.
SENATORS SANDERS AND HARRIS,
HAVE COME DOWN STRONGLY IN FAVOR
OF MEDICARE FOR ALL EVEN IF THAT
DOES MEAN THE END FOR PRIVATE
INSURANCE, HARRIS HAS
EQUIVOCATED ON WHETHER SHE'S IN
FAVOR OF MAINTAINING THAT OR
SOME PRIVATE INSURANCE.
THAT'S THE DEBATE WE'RE GOING TO
SEE PLAY OUT.
AND I THINK THE QUESTION FOR
THOSE WHO ARE OPPOSED TO
MEDICARE FOR ALL, AND AN END TO
PRIVATE INSURANCE, HOW STRONGLY
DO THEY MAKE THAT CASE.
ONE OF THE THINGS WE SAW IN THE
DEBATE, ALI, WAS SENATO BENNETT
SAYS THERE'S A MORE UNIVERSAL
WAY TO DO IT.
THAT'S THE DEBATE WE'RE GOING TO
SEE.
>> DAN, MOST DEVELOPED COUNTRIES
HAVE SOME FORM OF UNIVERSAL
CARE, UNIVERSAL INSURANCE
COVERAGE.
THERE ARE MANY WAYS TO GET AT
THIS.
MY SENSE COMING UP WITH MEDICARE
FOR ALL I HAPPEN TO LIKE AS A
CANADIAN BECAUSE IT'S VERY
SIMILAR TO THE SINGLE PAYER
SYSTEM IN CANADA.
BUT IT CONFUSES THE ISSUE-THERE
ARE PEOPLE IN FAVOR OF MEDICARE
FOR ALL.
THEN AS YOU SAY, WHEN YOU ADD IN
YOUR POLL DID, ADD IN THE
QUESTION, IS THAT OKAY IF YOU
ELIMINATE YOUR PRIVATE
INSURANCE, I THINK IT'S A LACK
OF UNDERSTANDING THAT PEOPLE
HAVE AGAINST THE VARIOUS
COMPETING SYSTEMS THAT ARE NOT
WHAT WE HAVE NOW.
>> WELL, THERE'S ALWAYS GOING TO
BE A MISUNDERSTANDING WHEN
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT TOTALLY
REVAMPING THE HEALTH CARE
SYSTEM.
WE SAW THAT IN THE DEBATE OVER
THE AFFORDABLE CARE ACT DURING
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION.
WE SAW THAT IN THE DEBATE OVER
THE CLINTON ADMINISTRATION.
EVERY TIME THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT AND CONGRESS HAVE
BEGUN TO TINKER, OR RADICALLY
CHANGE THE HEALTH CARE SYSTEM,
THERE IS A LOT OF
MISUNDERSTANDING.
AND THERE ARE A LOT OF CONCERNS
ON PART OF PEOPLE WHO ALREADY
HAVE INSURANCE.
ONE OF THE REALITIES IS, AS YOU
KNOW, UNDER OUR MEDICARE SYSTEM,
THERE IS PRIVATE INSURANCE.
MANY -- MOST, IF NOT ALL,
MEDICARE RECIPIENTS HAVE OR NEED
SOME KIND OF ADDITIONAL
INSURANCE TO PAY FOR THE COSTS
THAT ARE NOT COVERED BY
MEDICARE.
SO, THERE ARE ALL THESE ASPECTS
OF IT.
SO, PART OF IT IS A BROAD
DEBATE, KIND OF WHAT'S THE BEST
WAY.
ONE OF THE THINGS I THINK THE
CANDIDATES HAVE HEARD ON THE
CAMPAIGN TRAIL IS, BEYOND THE
QUESTION OF WHAT KIND OF SYSTEM
DO WE HAVE, THE QUESTION IS WHAT
DOES IT COST?
>> RIGHT.
>> HOW MUCH DOES IT COST?
AND PEOPLE'S CONCERNED ABOUT
RISING COSTS.
THAT'S ANOTHER ISSUE THAT HAS TO
BE DEALT WITH.
>> AGAIN, IT'S A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT THE CLIMATE CHANGE DEBATE,
RIGHT?
THERE'S A QUESTION OF WHAT
THINGS COST, BUT THERE ISN'T A
REALLY GOOD ACTUARIAL OR ACTUAL
CALCULATION OF THE COST OR COST
OF CURRENT SYSTEM.
WOULD IT BE EASIER FOR PEOPLE TO
DIGEST IF IT WAS WELL PRICED OUT
AND COMPARED TO, AND THIS IS
WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU DON'T?
>> WELL, THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
BUT AS WE'VE SEEN IN PAST
DEBATES, GETTING THOSE COST
ESTIMATES OR GETTING PEOPLE TO
AGREE ON THOSE COST ESTIMATES IS
A VERY, VERY DIFFICULT
PROPOSITION.
AND YOU GET THEM COMING FROM
PEOPLE WITH DIFFERENT
IDEOLOGICAL VIEWPOINTS.
AND DIFFERENT POLITICAL
VIEWPOINTS.
INTERESTS.
SO THE DEBATE OVER WHAT THE
ACTUAL COST IS AS DIFFICULT
SOMETIMES AS WHAT IS THE
STRUCTURE OF A NEW SYSTEM VERSUS
THE CURRENT SYSTEM.
>> DAN, THANK YOU FOR YOUR
THOROUGH COVERAGE.
>> COMING UP, HONORING LUIS
ALVAREZ, LAID TO REST TODAY.
HE'S A SEPTEMBER 11 FIRST
RESPONDER WHO FOUGHT TO CONGRESS
TO EXTEND HEALTH BENEFITS TO HIS
FELLOW 9/11 FIRST RESPONDERS.
AFTER THE BREAK I'M JOINED BY
CONGRESSWOMAN CAROLINE MALONEY
WHO HAS PLEDGED TO CONTINUE THE
FIGHT.
YOU'RE WATCHING MSNBC.
your home at a great price,
the way it works
best for you,
I'll take that. Wait honey, no.
when you want it.
You get a delivery
experience
you can always count on.
You get your perfect find at
a price to match,
on your own schedule.
You get FAST and FREE
shipping on the things that
make your home feel like you.
That's what you get
when you've got Wayfair.
So shop now!
If you have moderate to
severe psoriasis
or psoriatic arthritis,
little things
can be a big deal.
That's why there's Otezla.
Otezla is not an injection
or a cream.
It's a pill that treats
differently.
For psoriasis, 75% clearer
skin is achievable,
with reduced redness, thickness,
and scaliness of plaques.
For psoriatic arthritis, Otezla
is proven to reduce joint
swelling, tenderness, and pain.
And the Otezla Prescribing
information has no requirement
for routine lab monitoring.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Otezla.
It may cause severe diarrhea,
nausea, or vomiting.
Otezla is associated with an
increased risk of depression.
Tell your doctor if you have a
history of depression
or suicidal thoughts
or if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor your
weight and may stop treatment.
Upper respiratory tract
infection
and headache may occur.
Tell your doctor about
your medicines
and if you're pregnant
or planning to be.
Ready to treat differently
with a pill?
Otezla. Show more of you.
I switched to MiraLAX
for my constipation.
Ready to treat differently
with a pill?
Stimulant laxatives
forcefully stimulate
the nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX works with
the water in your
body to unblock your
system naturally.
And it doesn't cause
bloating,
cramping, gas,
or sudden urgency.
MiraLAX.
Look for the pink cap.
Cake in the conference room!
Showing 'em you're ready to be
your own boss.
That's the beauty of your smile.
Bring out the best in it with
Crest 3D White.
Crest removes 95% of surface
stains...
In just three days.
ALYSSA NAEHER.
>>> HUNDREDS GATHERED IN NEW
YORK CITY THIS MORNING TO MOURN
THE LOSS OF A SEPTEMBER 11 HERO.
53-YEAR-OLD NYPD DETECTIVE LUIS
ALVAREZ WAS LAID TO REST IN
QUEENS, NEW YORK.
HE DIED SATURDAY IN HOSS PIN
CARE FOLLOWING A THREE-YEAR
BATTLE WITH CANCER AND 60 ROUNDS
OF CHEMOTHERAPY.
ALVAREZ ATTRIBUTED HIS CANCER TO
THE THREE MONTHS HE SPENT AT
GROUND ZERO FOLLOWING THE
SEPTEMBER 11 ATTACKS.
PLEADED FOR BENEFITS FOR HIS
FELLOW 9/11 RESPONDERS.
>> I SHOULD NOT BE HERE WITH
YOU, BUT YOU MADE ME COME.
YOU MADE ME COME BECAUSE I WILL
NOT STAND BY AND WATCH AS MY
FRIENDS WITH CANCER FROM 9/11
LIKE ME ARE VALUED LESS THAN
ANYONE ELSE BECAUSE OF WHEN THEY
GET SICK, THEY DIE.
>> AMONG THE MANY WHO ATTENDED
WERE COMEDIAN AND ACTOR JON
STEWART, WHO JOINED HIM IN THE
FIGHT FOR THE HEALTH BENEFIT.
YOU SEE HIM HERE SALUTING
ALVAREZ IN THE FINAL GOOD-BYE.
NEXT YOU SEE NEW YORK
CONGRESSWOMAN MARIE MARONEY, WHO
WAS THERE TO PAY HER RESPECT TO
THE FALLEN HERO.
CONGRESSWOMAN, THANK YOU FOR
BEING WITH US.
>> THANK YOU FOR REMEMBERING AND
THANK YOU FOR REMEMBERING
DETECTIVE ALVAREZ.
>> WHAT WAS THE ATMOSPHERE GIVEN
HE WAS A WARRIOR REALLY.
>> THERE WAS A TREMENDOUS AMOUNT
OF SUPPORT.
THE POLICE DEPARTMENT WAS THERE
FROM THE HEAD HUNDREDS OF
POLICE, NOT ONLY FROM NEW YORK
BUT OTHER AREAS, HIS EXTENDED
FAMILY.
HE WAS AT THE PARISH HE WAS
RAISED IN AND MANY, MANY FRIENDS
AND FAMILY THERE.
IT WAS A HUGE GATHERING.
>> HE WAS BORN IN CUBA.
>> WHEN HE WAS ABOUT 6 YEARS OLD
AND RAISED IN THIS PARISH.
HE'S THE AMERICAN DREAM.
HE JOINED THE MARINES, JOINED
THE POLICE FORCE, WAS A
DECORATED OFFICER AND DETECTIVE
IN NARCOTICS AND LATER BOMBS.
I SAY HE'S A HERO, TRUE AMERICAN
HERO AND WORKING TO PASS THE
9/11 VICTIMS COMPENSATION FUND.
>> YOU REMEMBER BACK TO THOSE
DAYS.
WHAT DID WE GET WRONG ABOUT THIS
WHEN IT CAME TO THE FIRST
RESPONDERS?
>> NO ONE WILL FORGET THAT DAY
WHEN PEOPLE WERE RUNNING FAR
AWAY FROM THE BUILDINGS AND THE
FIRST RESPONDERS RAN THE OTHER
WAY.
>> THEY RAN INTO IT AND WE LOST
3,000 PEOPLE, MOST OF THEM
RESPONDERS ON THAT DAY.
AND WE WILL LOSE MANY MORE,
THOUSANDS MORE BECAUSE OF THOSE
THAT WORKED AT THE PILE.
AND IT'S A DOUBLE OUTRAGE IN A
SENSE BECAUSE NOT ONLY ARE THEY
VICTIMS OF THE WAR ON TERROR BUT
OUR GOVERNMENTS THAT SAID IT'S
SAFE, COME BACK AND WORK.
OF COURSE IT'S NOT.
>> THE EPA SAID IT WOULD BE
FACE.
MANY OF THESE PEOPLE, WE
REMEMBER THAT PLUME THAT WENT
ON --
>> SIX MONTHS.
>> YOU COULD SEE IT.
YOU COULD SMELL IT, ANYWHERE IN
NEW YORK.
>> IT WAS HORRIBLE.
>> THEY WORRIED ABOUT THAT.
THEY WERE GOING TO DO THEIR JOBS
AND THEY WERE GOING TO CONTINUE
TO DO THEIR JOBS BUT THEY
WORRIED THEY WERE IN DANGER AT
THE TIME AND THEY WERE TOLD BY
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT THEY WERE
SAFE.
FOR THOSE WHO SAY THIS IS A NEW
YORK PROBLEM, THEY WERE RELYING
ON INFORMATION FROM THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT SAYING YOU'RE GOOD,
KEEP ON WORKING.
>> YOU GOT IT RIGHT.
NOT ONLY IS THERE A
RESPONSIBILITY AS VETERANS
AGAINST TERROR BUT THEY'RE ALSO
THE VETERANS OF MISINFORMATION
FROM THE GOVERNMENT THEY SERVED.
WE COULD NEVER REPAY WHAT THEY
GAVE, THEIR LIFE AND HEALTH.
BUT THIS IS ONE WAY WE CAN MAKE
THEIR LIVES BETTER AND THOSE OF
THEIR FAMILIES THAT MANY OF THEM
ARE LEAVING BEHIND.
THEY ARE NOT THERE TO PROTECT
THEM.
WE NEED TO GIVE THEM SUPPORT.
>> DO YOU BELIEVE THIS IS GOING
TO GET DONE?
>> I BELIEVE IT WILL GET DOWN
AND I'M HOPING TO GET IT ON THE
FLOOR FOR A VOTE NEXT WEEK AND
SEND IT TO THE SENATE WHERE
MITCH McCONNELL SAYS HE HOPES TO
PASS AND IT WILL PASS IT FROM
THE AUGUST RECESS.
KEEPING AT HIS WORD, LET'S GET
OUR WORK DONE IN THE HOUSE AND
SEND THE BILL OVER TO HIM.
>> CONGRESSWOMAN MALONEY, THANK
YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
It all comes down
to a single defining moment...
...when a plan stops being a
plan and gets set into motion.
Today's Merrill
can help you get there
with the people, tools,
and personalized advice
to help turn your ambitions
into action.
What would you like
the power to do?
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 65 AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
WE REMEMBER THIS HOUR BY
REMEMBERING THE GUY WHO
REVOLUTIONIZED THE AUTO
INDUSTRY.
DE-IACOCCA, WHO BECAME FORD'S
PRESIDENT AFTER SUCCESSES
INCLUDING THE CREATION OF THE
FORD MUSTANG.
HE MADE HIS MARK AS CHAIRMAN OF
RIVAL AUTOMAKER CHRYSLER WHO
SAVED THE COMPANY BEFORE
BANKRUPTCY BY INTRODUCING T