and they literally
gave all they had.
Narrator:
And for the prosecutors,
the Telexfree fraud
is one for the record books.
Lelling: The success
of the pyramid scheme
and the speed with which it grew
and took over the world
is unlike any other fraud case
I've done
in about 15 years
as a fraud prosecutor.
To do that much damage
in that short a period
was really amazing
and just showed you
how dangerous
these kinds of scams are.
♪♪
-- Captions by VITAC --
Narrator: In this episode
of "American Greed"...
Glafira Rosales is a novice
to the New York art scene,
but she has all the right moves.
She really played
the relationships right.
Narrator: She says
she holds the key
to a treasure trove of
never-before-seen masterpieces.
Jackson Pollock with
famous drip paintings,
Mark Rothko,
Robert Motherwell.
These are paintings that go
for millions of dollars each.
Narrator: A tale
with enough mystique
to draw millionaire buyers...
Collectors are greedy
for recognition
and for artwork
that lends them prestige.
Narrator: But before
you open your wallet,
you may want to look twice...
Every aspect of the story
behind those paintings
was a red flag.
Narrator: It turns out
skilled forgers
know how to splash paint, too...
Glafira Rosales was able
to take 63 paintings,
get $33 million dollars
out of them,
and then the galleries sold them
for $81 million dollars.
Narrator: And Glafira Rosales
is a modern master
in the art of the con.
The experts believed it.
Collectors bought it.
It was auctioned off
by big auction houses.
I mean, this woman was sitting
on top of the world.
♪♪
Teeming with galleries, museums,
and hundreds of art dealers,
New Yorkers work hard to keep
their art capital booming.
♪♪
So in 2011,
when one of New York's
most venerable art galleries
suddenly closes its doors,
the art world is in shock.
Knoedler & Company has been
in business since 1846
and according to
art historian Jack Flam,
they've held
a sterling pedigree.
Knoedler & Company had one
of the largest reputations
of any art gallery
in the country
and one of
the largest reputations
of any gallery in the world.
Narrator: Its legacy was built
by supplying art
to Gilded Age tycoons like
Cornelius Vanderbilt,
John D. Rockefeller,
and J.P. Morgan.
Over the years it evolved.
It handled old master paintings.
It handled modern
master paintings.
And then from around 1970 or so,
handled contemporary art.
And in each one
of those domains,
it really handled
Blue-Chip Art.
Narrator: Knoedler's closing
after 165 years is surprising,
but the real kicker comes
when rumors start to surface
that Knoedler is embroiled
in a massive art fraud.
People who had bought paintings
from Knoedler
were coming forward,
having their paintings
forensically tested.
And soon former federal
prosecutor Jason Hernandez
and U.S. investigators
will prove that a supplier
provided the gallery with fakes,
sold for millions of dollars
to some of America's
wealthiest collectors.
What those paintings represented
would have been
one of the greatest finds
of the abstract
American Expressionist school.
And these are paintings that go
for millions of dollars each.
Narrator: Knoedler,
along with the gallery's
director Ann Freedman,
say they've been fleeced
just like their clients
by a persuasive swindler
named Glafira Rosales.
Glafira Rosales is
an incredibly sophisticated
con artist.
Narrator: Maria Konnikova
is the author
of "The Confidence Game,"
a book about fraudsters.
She became intrigued
with the story
when the rumors
started to erupt.
What drew me to it
wasn't just kind of the glamour
of the art fraud world,
but how it is that
incredibly smart people
sometimes believe things that,
to an outsider,
seem incredibly dumb.
Narrator: According
to court documents,
Glafira Rosales
and her boyfriend,
Jose Carlos Bergantiños Diaz,
arrive in the U.S. sometime
in the early 1980s.
We don't know that much about
what her life was like
in Mexico,
which was her home country.
We know that she worked
in different jobs
in the United States,
some in the art field.
Narrator: First,
they settle in Houston,
where Glafira waits tables
and Jose finds work
as a kitchen helper.
It takes them little over a year
to earn enough money
to move to the real
city of dreams --
New York.
In 1986, Rosales is granted
permanent residence.
She and Jose Bergantiños
have a daughter
and buy a small house
in the suburbs.
Rosales even fulfills
her childhood aspiration
and opens a small
gallery business called
"King's Fine Art."
Konnikova: What Glafira Rosales
told people was that
she was from a family
that loved art,
that had a lot of people come
to their house for art salons.
And so from a very young age,
she was fascinated
by this world.
Narrator: Sometime later,
Rosales meets
a well-liked figure
in the New York art scene,
who happens to hold a position
at Knoedler Gallery.
He offers to set up a meeting
with the gallery's director,
Ann Freedman.
Konnikova: Ann Freedman
was pretty new
as the director of Knoedler.
She'd been very successful
in her art career
and someone who knows
how to sell things to people,
which is what you need
in the art world.
But now she really wanted
to make a mark
as the female director of
this really prominent gallery.
Narrator: As luck would have it,
Rosales is looking
to make her mark, too.
So in 1995,
when 40 year-old
Glafira Rosales
breezes into Knoedler & Company
with a canvas,
she's the epitome
of a well-dressed
and cultivated art dealer.
Lawyer Luke Nikas
represented Ann Freedman
in what's been called
"the art trial of the century."
You have a woman
who's unassuming.
She's not slick.
She doesn't have this
well-planned story.
She's got a relationship
with a man
who inherited the painting
from his father,
and he lived in Mexico.
And he just wanted to get rid
of this collection.
Narrator: Freedman leads
Rosales upstairs
to a small drawing room.
The painting's warm
peachy background
with two ethereal
clouds of color
is immediately recognizable
as the work of Mark Rothko --
a leading artist of the
abstract-expressionist movement.
Rothko, along with
Jackson Pollock,
Robert Motherwell,
and a few select others,
were leaders of the abstract-
expressionist movement
that emerged in New York
during the 1940s.
That handful of artists
are the artists
that are the most valued,
have the largest reputation,
and in some cases,
also fetch the highest prices.
Narrator: People don't
walk in off the street
carrying a Rothko,
and Ann Freedman knows it.
When questioned,
Rosales spins her tale
of growing up in a prominent
Catholic family in Mexico,
surrounded by the crème de
la crème of society.
That's where Glafira
came in contact
with the heir to a secret
art collection --
a man she refers to only
as "Mr. X."
To begin, she would try
to sell the collection
of a painter friend,
someone whose confidentiality
she wanted to respect
and so he became known
as Mr. X.
Narrator: Mr. X's father
had been a patron
of the abstract expressionist
art scene.
He purchased artworks straight
from the artist's studios,
paying in cash,
so the assets and taxes
were never declared.
According to Rosales,
there's another family secret
that needs to be kept...
Flam: This man was
married and had a family
and he was a closet homosexual,
and in Mexico, supposedly,
it was dangerous to be
a homosexual at that time.
And so the man had died
and now his son was selling
the pictures,
but he wanted to do it
as discreetly as possible.
Narrator: But there's a bonus,
and it's alluring.
This Rothko is just the tip
of the iceberg.
Her secretive client
has a collection
of previously unknown works
by Robert Motherwell,
Willem de Kooning,
Jackson Pollock, and more.
A Pollock painting in 2015
went for $200 million.
Only a few years before that,
a Rothko went
for $86 million dollars.
They're really big numbers
involved.
Narrator: This collection has
been hidden in storage
for decades.
But Rosales is not an expert
in abstract expressionism
and her own gallery
is too small.
It doesn't seem to matter
that few in the art world
have heard of Rosales...
This art is some of the most
valued art of the 20th century.
People paid tens of millions
of dollars for it,
and we haven't had anything new
in it for a while.
Narrator: The gallery's
new director, Ann Freedman,
is dazzled by the prospect
and profits.
Up next on "American Greed"...
Rosales' promise
of a trove of masterworks
is too good to pass up.
Can you imagine being
the one to discover
this previously-unknown
treasure trove
of abstract expressionist art?
You're not just making a name
for yourself,
but you are becoming the name.
♪♪
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it from
your allergy pills?
Flonase Sensimist relieves
all your worst symptoms,
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
And all from a gentle mist
you can barely feel.
Flonase Sensimist.
Oh milk. Am I willing to pay
the price for loving you?
You'll make my morning, but
ruin my day.
Complicated relationship with
milk?
Pour on the Lactaid, 100% real
milk,
just without that annoying
lactose.
Mmm, that's good.
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now with T-mobile get the
Samsung Galaxy S10e included
With unlimited data for just $40
a month.
♪
Congrats, Kim!
You got your own car,
with your own insurance.
No more driving
that old hand-me-down.
Did you trade it in?
My parents handed it
down to my little brother.
You ready?
Yeah...
SURPRISE!
No. Not Beige Betty!
You guys can't
do this to me, seriously?!
My car is like
a rite of passage.
How do you expect
me to drive this?!
Just turn the key...
and yeah, it's just uh...
Some of this...
...it's automatic...
...dual cupholders.
Go with the one that's
here to help life go right.
State Farm.
The communal feast.
Potluck.
This parade of dishes will soon
be yours to scrub.
And they're not even...
Yours.
New and improved Dawn Ultra can
finish off this buffet.
Each drop now has even more
grease-cleaning power.
So you can scrub 50% less,
and get done faster.
Next month, their place!
A drop of Dawn and grease is
gone.
Narrator: Up until now,
Glafira Rosales
has been circling the fringes
of the New York art scene.
She didn't know that much
about art,
to be perfectly honest,
but she picked up a lot
from the people around her.
Narrator: Her new contact,
Ann Freedman,
the director
of Knoedler Gallery,
has the power to launch her
into the upper echelons.
Glafira was delivering
a great product
that she knew would
catch the attention
of the right people.
Narrator: Glafira's portrayal
of the unassuming novice
is picture perfect.
I always think
about the excitement
that Ann Freedman felt,
like the excitement
you might feel
finding dinosaur bones.
It's this unearthed discovery.
Narrator: But a slight
drawback emerges --
the recorded history
of ownership
that proves its authenticity
is called "provenance,"
and this one is murky.
Hernandez: Provenance is
a really important concept
in the art world.
The story was that they were
purchased by a family,
a collector,
directly from the artist,
often purchased outside
the back of the gallery
in exchange for cash,
and they had been kept
in storage,
basically, for decades.
So if you believe that story,
the lack of provenance
actually makes sense.
Narrator: So over the next
decade, Glafira Rosales
provides Knoedler with a few
new paintings each year,
all by heavy hitters.
She sells additional works
to art broker Julian Weissman --
another New York art dealer.
♪♪
Her anonymous collector, Mr. X,
turns out to be the gift horse
that keeps on giving.
The most high-profile artists --
Jackson Pollocks, Rothkos,
Motherwell's.
I mean, you name it,
it was there.
Narrator: And discretion
is fundamental
to the rare-art market,
where collectors are often
tightlipped about selling.
Hernandez: Secrecy is highly
prized in the art world.
When you're a buyer,
you're not entitled,
for example,
to know who the seller is,
or if a broker comes in
with a piece of art,
they don't have to necessarily
disclose who their client is.
Narrator: Still, Rosales'
secret collector
poses a vexing setback
when it comes
to negotiating prices.
The more provenance you have,
the more detail you have,
the more likely the work is
gonna sell for a higher price,
because the backup is there.
Narrator: When Ann Freedman
pushes her for more details,
Rosales names David Herbert,
a deceased New York art dealer
as the go-between.
She hears the name David Herbert
as someone who has been
associated with these artists,
who was also part of
the gay community at the time.
And so, all of a sudden,
David Herbert can be someone
who's connected to Mr. X.
Narrator: To help shore up
the murky provenance,
Knoedler shows the works
to art experts
to get their opinions.
Ann Freedman, Knoedler Gallery
showed these paintings,
including the very first one
that came in the door
to some of the finest experts
in the world on Mark Rothko.
They saw these paintings,
several of them,
and said these are convincing.
Narrator: Art historian
Jack Flam recalls
viewing a painting at Knoedler
by Robert Motherwell.
Flam: She showed me
a Motherwell elegy
that was on the floor
in her office
and she said that
she had just got it.
Flam had been close friends
with Motherwell
until his death in 1991.
The work is credited
to Motherwell's Spanish
elegy series --
and it catches him
by surprise.
Flam: In the elegies, which
became his signature paintings.
From 1948 to when he died,
in 1991,
he painted over
a 170 elegy paintings.
They're also
the paintings of his
that fetch the highest prices
on the market.
Narrator: Freedman
never mentions
the name Glafira Rosales.
Instead, the works
are generally referred to
as "the Herbert Collection."
And she asked me if I remember
correctly, at that time,
whether I had ever heard
of someone named David Herbert.
And I said, "No, I had not."
And she said, "He was
a well-known art dealer."
And, you know, at the time,
I thought, "Well, you know,
that's nice."
Narrator: Jack Flam doesn't
think of questioning
Knoedler's rock-solid
reputation.
And so, you know,
you're in Knoedler,
you don't think twice.
Narrator: And, of course,
there's that added boon
for buyers who are willing
to accept
the lack of documentation.
Man: 1,400,000 is bid.
These are artists that are
really, really difficult to get
and that command
incredibly high prices.
Now imagine you can
get those works,
and at a bargain price.
So not only are you
a brilliant art collector,
you're also a pretty
genius businessman.
Narrator: Some collectors are
more wary than others.
Rosales sells this purported
Jackson Pollock to Knoedler
for $750,000.
In 2001, Knoedler turns around
and sells it to Jack Levy,
a co-chairman at Goldman Sachs,
for $2 million.
With one caveat --
The sale hinges on Knoedler
obtaining a review
verifying its authenticity
from the International
Foundation for Art Research --
otherwise known as "IFAR."
Nikas: It had a panel
of experts put together
to give their views
about the painting,
and they wrote a report.
Narrator: But IFAR won't
positively attribute
the work to Pollock
and deems the provenance
questionable.
Knoedler discreetly cancels
Levy's sale
and refunds his $2 million,
but Knoedler's mission
is to sell.
Nikas: These works were
really exciting.
And some really smart,
prominent people
bought these works
for their collections.
Narrator: A California collector
pays $3.1 million
for a painting said to be
by Jackson Pollock.
John Howard, who runs
a billion dollar equity firm,
purchases a Willem de Kooning
for $4 million.
In 2004, Domenico de Sole,
a chairman of Tom Ford
and Sotheby's,
buys a purported Rothko
for $8.3 million.
♪♪
Next, while Rosales
and her gallery clients
are celebrating
their lucrative alliance
and million-dollar sales...
eyes are on another painting
that's popped up
on the market...
I had certain kind of,
in my gut,
misgivings about it.
♪♪
I can't believe it.
That we're playing
“four on four”
with a barbershop quartet?
[QUARTET SINGING]
Bum bum bum bum...
pass the ball... pass the rock..
...we're open
just pass the ball!
No, I can't believe how easy it
was to save hundreds of dollars
on my car
insurance with GEICO.
Yea.
[QUARTET SINGING]
Shoot the J! Shoot, shoot,
shoot the jaaaaaay...
Believe it! GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
or more on car insurance.
Believe it! GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
AT&T provides Edge-to-Edge
Intelligence,
covering virtually every part of
your healthcare business.
So that if she has a heart
problem
& the staff needs to know, they
will
& they'll drop everything
Can you take a look at her
vitals?
& share the data with other
specialists
Yeah, I'm looking at them now.
& they'll drop everything
Hey.
& take care of this baby
Yeah, that procedure seems
right.
& that one too.
AT&T provides Edge to Edge
Intelligence.
It can do so much for your
business,
the list goes on and on.
That's the power of &.
& when your patient's tests come
back...
♪ All the ways, all the ways ♪
♪ Tell me all the ways  ♪
♪ And he said ♪
♪ Girl, you take care of me ♪
♪ You are my therapy ♪
♪ The better half of me ♪
♪ Say it again ♪
♪ If you love me,
love me, love me ♪
♪ Like you say ♪
♪ Darling tell me all the ways ♪
♪ Tell me all the ways ♪
Now, we're bringing
you all the ways
to get what you need.
Target Run and Done.
By 2006, the market
for Abstract Expressionist art
is enjoying a renaissance,
thanks in part
to Glafira Rosales' collection
of never-before-seen
masterpieces.
For works by major artists
to come up on the market,
it's extremely rare.
But for multiple works
by the same artist
to come out of
the same collection
is very, very unusual.
Narrator: The alliance between
the little-known Rosales
and a prestigious gallery
like Knoedler
might seem strange, too.
But it appears to be kismet.
Rosales just built, slowly,
this relationship of trust.
She would talk to Ann about
her daughter's musical talent.
She would talk with her
every single birthday.
This was the sort of thing
that really made Ann Freedman
trust Glafira Rosales.
Narrator: While Rosales
is the supplier,
Ann Freedman is the face
that makes the sales.
Meridith Savona was formerly
with the FBI's art crimes unit.
She offers an analogy
of Knoedler's prestige.
If I buy a diamond
from Tiffany's,
I'm not going to then take it
to find out if it's authentic.
I bought it from Tiffany's.
If I buy a painting
from Knoedler Gallery,
I have to assume
it's an authentic painting.
It had that same kind
of reputation.
Hernandez:
Often, there'll be experts
who in their heart of hearts
think that a painting is fake,
but they'll never express it.
And part of that is due
to the politeness
of the art business,
but really it's also driven
by the fear of being sued.
Narrator: So in January 2007,
art historian Jack Flam
is at odds when
a Robert Motherwell painting
pops up at Julian Weissman's,
another New York art broker.
We had no record of it,
and this is always
very exciting,
to see a new painting.
The "Spanish Elegy" reminds him
of the Motherwell he saw
in Freedman's office before...
But there's something strange
in the details.
I had certain kind of,
in my gut,
misgivings about it.
It was by then 50 years old
or more --
and although it was warped
the front of it,
the paint was not warped
or cracked,
which looked odd.
Narrator: He holds his tongue,
despite his misgivings.
Flam: You're always advised
not to police the market.
It's not your job.
But, nonetheless, you want
to protect your artist legacy.
Narrator: As it happens,
Flam is also president
of the Dedalus Foundation,
founded by Robert Motherwell.
Dedalus is in the midst
of compiling
a catalogue raisonné
on Motherwell.
A catalogue raisonné
is a gathering
of all the works by an artist.
By common usage,
it becomes the standard
for establishing what are the
authentic works by the artist
and what is
their authentic history.
Narrator: During the process,
researchers track down
every known work by Motherwell.
They enter it
into their database
and assign it an ID number.
And you see the difference
in the late '58.
I still kept that sense
of spontaneity.
While studying seven paintings
attributed to Motherwell's
"Spanish Elegy" series,
they notice a striking anomaly.
My team showed me digital images
on the fronts and the backs
of the Spanish Elegies.
And there were six from 1953,
and this new one was 1955.
When we saw the back
of this one,
we saw that it was signed
very much the way
the others were.
For example, Robert Motherwell,
and then underneath it
the date, 1955.
And then on a painting that was
supposed to have been done
three years earlier, in 1953,
once again,
"Spanish Elegy"
in quotation marks
and full caps on the top, almost
exactly the same printing,
and the date in the same place.
Narrator:
But Motherwell's signature
is known to be inconsistent.
Flam: Motherwell, in particular,
signed pictures in different
ways, in different months.
So, this was a real tell.
This really made us suspicious.
Narrator: Another tell has to do
with the two words --
"Spanish Elegy."
Flam:
Now, this is something that
Motherwell himself often said,
"My Spanish Elegy paintings."
Or "That's a Spanish Elegy."
But he did not put that
on the backs of the paintings.
And this is especially
significant
because those paintings
that we were beginning
to suspect were fakes
had the title
"Spanish Elegy" on them.
Narrator: Another "tell,"
and the perhaps most damning
in Flam's mind,
has to do with technique.
As you look at the crispness
and the intensity with which
the real paint is painted,
and you look at this,
which is all kind of muffled
and soft around the edges.
Motherwell was very proud of
and very careful about
is the way in which
he used variations of edge.
So, you get very sharp edges,
very soft edges.
So, that kind of variation is
something very important to him,
but the, something that
the forger misses entirely.
Narrator: Their findings
leave no doubt to Flam
that the elegies are fake.
For Dedalus, it just
begs the question,
"Where did these pictures
come from?"
And going through the database,
we found that none
of these pictures
had a provenance that went
back before 1999.
First owner for four of them
Ann Freedman, Knoedler Gallery.
Other three, Julian Weissman.
This is more than bizarre.
You got seven paintings.
Four of them come
from one gallery
and they were almost like
one from one gallery,
the next year,
one from the other,
one from one,
one from the other.
♪♪
Up next, more questions arise
about Rosales' elusive
collector, Mr. X.
Flam: I had come to suspect
that Mr. X did not exist.
Every aspect of the story
behind those paintings
was a red flag.
♪♪
Sweat.
Dedication.
Cupcakes.
I'm Michael Griffin.
I'm Brian Orakpo.
We played football together for
the Titans.
Now, we own a cupcake shop.
We bake, we decorate.
I love this new Surface Pro.
It's light, it's sleek, it's
fast.
I'm able to draw what color
frosting we want.
We do a lot with social media.
We have funny videos that we do
in the bakery.
There's nothing that you can't
do on this device.
Cupcakes are a great business.
Oh yeah, as long as you don't
eat the profits!
♪ ♪
[peaceful acoustic guitar]
(male announcer)
We know these memories
will last longer
than the wrapping paper.
We know there's some things
you just can't put a bow on.
We know the best gift of all
is still out there.
We know the Great Outdoors.
We love the
Great Outdoors.
Bass Pro Shops and Cabela's--
Where incredible selection,
great people,
and an experience like no other
all come together.
♪♪
[elevator bell]
Yup.
Little choices make
a big difference.
Like delicious fruits
and veggies.
However You Healthy.
Naked.
[music playing]
(VO)
This is Jerry.
Jerry has a
membership to this gym,
but he's not using it.
And he has subscriptions to a
music service he doesn't listen
to and five streaming video
services he doesn't watch.
This is Jerry learning that
he's still paying for this stuff
he's not using.
He's seeing his recurring
payments in Control Tower
in the Wells Fargo Mobile app.
This is Jerry canceling
a few things. Booyah.
This is Jerry appreciating the
people who made this possible.
Oh look, there they are.
(Team Member)
This is Wells Fargo.
[farmers bell]
(Driver)
Relax, it's just a bug.
That's not a bug,
that's not a bug!
(Burke)
Hit and Drone.
Seen it, covered it.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
The art market can
be secretive.
Sometimes super-rich
buyers and sellers
opt for discretion --
sellers like Glafira Rosales.
Nikas: Glafira
wasn't ostentatious.
She didn't have flashy clothes.
She didn't have
an extraordinary mansion
that $30 million can buy.
She had a nice home
on Long Island.
She had a nice authentic
collection of art
and she lived a good life.
But brokering art for
her anonymous client, Mr. X,
has put plenty of money
in her pocket.
The most lucrative sale comes
in November 2007,
when hedgefund billionaire,
Pierre Lagrange,
buys a Jackson Pollock painting
from Knoedler for $17 million.
Hernandez: So over the course
of 15 years,
Glafira Rosales was able
to take 63 paintings,
get $33 million out of them,
and then the galleries sold them
for $81 million.
Narrator: At this point,
Jack Flam
and researchers
from the Dedalus Foundation
appeared to be
the only skeptics.
In fact, Flam finds the story
of Mr. X astounding.
Flam: And you know, this sounded
like a classic, you know,
"These paintings were given
to my aunt by her lover."
And you know,
"Nobody was supposed
to know about the lover,
and now the lover's dead
and she wants to sell
the paintings."
I mean, this is a classic story
for fronting fake paintings.
Narrator: He lays out his
suspicions to Ann freedman,
the director
of Knoedler Gallery.
My expectation was that
she would be grateful
because we're alerting her
to a possible fraud,
and therefore,
she could take action.
She could go back to the person
she was getting them from
and say,
"Hey, what's the story?"
And instead, she started
arguing with us.
Narrator:
While Ann Freedman declined
to speak with "American Greed,"
Lawyer Luke Nikas defended her
in later civil cases.
Nikas: Ann Freedman
believed in these works
as she spent the better part
of 14 years
doing diligence in them,
hiring experts to research them.
And she really believed in them.
So, this was very disturbing.
We had no doubt that
the paintings were wrong,
that Ann was being hoodwinked
by someone.
Narrator: In December 2008,
Dedalus refuses to enter
the newly discovered works
in their catalogue raisonné.
Flam: The vast majority
of people
who own works by an artist,
they want it to be
in the catalogue raisonné,
because this is
a sign of authenticity.
Narrator:
To mitigate their concerns,
Knoedler agrees to submit
the "Spanish Elegy"
to forensic testing.
They run an arsenal of tests,
including infrared spectroscopy,
to help determine whether or not
certain materials are present
in a painting.
The results...
There was paint that was found
that didn't exist at the time
of some of these artists.
Narrator: In particular,
the presence
of acrylic polymer
emulsion paints.
But Robert Motherwell did not
begin using this kind of paint
until the 1960s.
Based on the findings,
the Dedalus Foundation
refuses to stand by
any of the seven
Motherwell elegies.
As rumors ripple
though the art scene,
more collectors are eyeing
their paintings.
Everyone who knew
this body of work,
whether they thought
the paintings were real
or whether they thought
the paintings were fakes,
all said the same thing,
"If one of them is fake,
they're all fake."
Narrator:
Flam makes the decision
to quietly contact the FBI.
Jack Flam is probably the hero
of this story,
because the FBI
was involved early on.
But he kept it very quiet,
and other people who knew what
was going on kept it very quiet,
which is the way that we can
do our investigations.
Narrator: Next on
"American Greed,"
what will it take to stop
a fraud?
Savona: From the time
the painting was created
to where it walked
through Knoedler,
there was nothing but gaps.
There was no paperwork.
There was no trail.
There was no records.
Want inside information
from the show?
Join the Greed social network.
Like us on American Greed's
Facebook page.
We'll be right back.
Great news, Liberty
Mutual customizes-
♪♪
Uh uh - I deliver
the news around here.
♪  ♪
Sources say Liberty
Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay
for what you need.
Over to you, logo.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
We're Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh and
you may remember us from...
Your very first sandwich,
Your move-in-day...feast.
Your bold canine caper.
[child] That's not for you,
Bandit!
Your dinner in the dark.
Your mammoth masterpiece.
[whispering] Your 3:47 AM snack.
And...whatever happened here...
Because we make Deli Fresh
with all the good of the deli,
no artificial preservatives and
no added nitrates or nitrites.
Make every sandwich count
with Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh.
(ATLAS)
Inferior phone detected.
(WOMAN)
What is happening?!?!
(ATLAS)
You need a new phone.
At Sprint, the new Samsung
Galaxy S10 series has arrived.
(WOMAN)
Wow.
(ATLAS)
And when you lease any of the
new Galaxy phones,
you get a Galaxy S10e from
Sprint to use.
(PAUL)
And Sprint's LTE Advanced
Network is built for Unlimited.
(ATLAS)
It's up to two times faster than
before.
(WOMAN)
No way.
(ATLAS)
Way. The data does not lie.
Punch it, Paul.
(AVO)
Switch to Sprint today.
Get a Samsung Galaxy S10e on us
when you lease your
next generation Galaxy phone.
For people with hearing loss,
visit Sprintrelay.com
Our everyday diet is
very acidic.
It can cause damage to
the enamel.
With the new Pronamel Repair
toothpaste
we can help actively repair
enamel
in its weakened state.
It's innovative.
With Pronamel Repair, more
minerals
are able to enter deep into the
enamel surface.
The fact that you have an
opportunity to repair
what's already been damaged,
it's amazing.
I think my go-to toothpaste is
going to be Pronamel
Repair.
TO BE NOBODY BUT YOURSELF IN A
WORLD WHICH IS DOING IT'S BEST
TO MAKE YOU EVERYBODY ELSE...
♪ ♪ ♪
MEANS TO FIGHT
THE HARDEST BATTLE,
WHICH ANY HUMAN BEING
CAN FIGHT AND NEVER STOP.
DOES THIS SOUND DISMAL?
IT ISN'T.
♪ ♪ ♪
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL LIFE ON EARTH.
♪ ♪ ♪
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL LIFE ON EARTH.
Narrator: By 2009,
Glafira Rosales
is enjoying a long
and lucrative run
as the supplier
of coveted masterpieces.
The market got hotter
and hotter,
and it was something
that Glafira Rosales
was able to take advantage of.
Narrator: She's
the biggest blessing
the art market has seen
in decades.
But the gravy train
is about to derail.
So it turned out that I was
not the only person
who thought that paintings that
were coming through Knoedler
and Julian Weissman were fake.
But people weren't talking
to each other.
Narrator: British billionaire
Pierre Lagrange
who bought a $17 million
Jackson Pollock from Knoedler
in 2007 is ready to let it go.
But suddenly, he's having
trouble unloading it...
He tried to sell it at one
of the big auction houses,
and they refused to sell it.
And because of Jack Flam's tip,
the FBI art crimes unit
is now curious about
the slew of paintings
attributed to the same
elusive provenance.
We had to go down every avenue
to find the negative,
to find that Mr. X.
did not exist,
to find that the client
did not exist.
Narrator: When former
assistant U.S. attorney
Jason Hernandez joins the case,
his first objective is clear.
To get a criminal prosecution
for fraud,
you have to prove
beyond a reasonable doubt
that someone intended
to commit a fraud
and that's the highest burden
in our law.
Narrator: Rosales may be
the likeliest suspect,
but it's not that simple.
Hernandez: You want to try
and figure out
some link to an artist,
to a manufacturing facility,
to purchases
that are suspicious.
Anything that would
give us a clue
as to who's making the paintings
and where they're coming from.
Narrator:
But every lead fizzles.
He decides to dig at it
from another angle --
the Internal Revenue Service.
Savona: I had never worked
with the IRS before,
and I thought, "Oh, man, now,
this is going to take forever."
And it didn't.
Enter IRS Special Agent
Eric Jonke
to follow the money.
It's hard to walk away
from bank statements,
wire transfers, and payments.
Narrator: Between
2006 and 2011,
Rosales asked the galleries
to deposit her payments
to two Spanish bank accounts --
BBVA and CAJA Madrid.
During the three years
of the investigation
that we took into consideration,
she received over $14 million
from prominent New York City
galleries for the work --
works of art that
she was selling.
Narrator: And central
to Rosales' story
is that she's an art broker
for her Spanish client.
If that's true,
she would pay 90%
to her mysterious client
and collect a standard fee
of 10%.
She says she's representing
somebody.
Well, it's obviously got to go
back to somebody.
And if it's not going back
to the person
she claims to be representing...
then there is nobody
she's representing.
Jonke: The biggest red flag
was her sending the money
directly overseas after selling
the pieces of artwork.
The nail in the coffin was that
she wasn't paying any clients.
Narrator: In particular,
Glafira Rosales'
mysterious client, Mr. X.
What that told us was,
that her story was false.
There is no family in Europe
that owns these paintings.
These are paintings that
are almost certainly fake
and that she's
pulling off a scam
and keeping the money
in foreign bank accounts.
The bank accounts link
to two new suspects --
her long-time boyfriend,
Carlos Bergantiños Diaz,
and his brother Jesus.
While it strengthens
the fraud case,
it also breaks another case
wide open --
tax evasion.
During 2006-2008, we saw
her receive a ton of money
and majority of it
sent overseas.
So we were able to look at that
and see how much she reported
on her tax returns.
She was reporting just
over $2 million received
for those three years,
when in fact,
she was receiving
over $14 million.
She was reporting peanuts
on her tax returns.
So from there,
she's understating her income,
lying on her tax returns,
and she's also hiding the
Spanish bank accounts overseas.
Narrator: In May 2013,
Glafira Rosales is charged
and held for tax fraud
and money laundering.
If convicted of all counts,
she's looking at up
to 34 years in prison.
In the ensuing weeks,
Pierre Lagrange sends Knoedler
an expert's report that
the Jackson Pollock painting
he purchased for $17 million
is yet another fake.
One day later, the long-esteemed
gallery closes its doors.
Hernandez: Over 60
of these paintings
spanning multiple artists.
But it was really only towards
the end of the scheme
that the full picture
was really brought to bear.
Narrator: Up next,
Glafira Rosales reveals
the shocking source
behind the scheme
that duped the art world
for millions.
I was very surprised
when I found out it was one man
who had done
all of those paintings.
♪♪
Woman 1: I had no
symptoms of Hepatitis C.
Man 1: Mine...
...caused liver damage.
VO: EPCLUSA treats all
main types of chronic Hep C.
VO: Whatever your type,
ask your doctor if EPCLUSA
is your kind of cure.
Woman 2: I had the common type.
Man 2: Mine was rare.
VO: EPCLUSA has a 98%
overall cure rate.
Man 3: I just found out
about my hepatitis C.
Woman 3: I knew for years.
VO: EPCLUSA is only one pill,
once a day, taken with
or without food for 12 weeks.
VO: Before starting EPCLUSA,
your doctor will test if you
have had hepatitis B,
which may flare up,
and could cause serious
liver problems during
and after treatment.
VO: Tell your doctor if you
have had hepatitis B,
other liver or kidney problems,
HIV, or other
medical conditions...
VO: ...and all medicines you
take,
including herbal supplements.
VO: Taking amiodarone with
EPCLUSA
may cause a serious slowing
of your heart rate.
VO: Common side effects include
headache and tiredness.
VO: Ask your doctor today,
if EPCLUSA is your kind of cure.
♪
Pardon the interruption but this
is big!
Now with T-mobile get the
Samsung Galaxy S10e included
With unlimited data for just $40
a month.
♪♪
[elevator bell]
Yup.
Little choices make
a big difference.
Like delicious fruits
and veggies.
However You Healthy.
I have a vision
Ncorrection number,
But I'm more than a number.
When I'm not teaching,
I'm taking steep grades
and tight corners.
My Essilor lenses offer more
than vision correction
with three innovative
technologies
For my ultimate in vision
Clarity
And Protection
Together in a single lens:
The Essilor Ultimate
Lens Package.
So, I can do more
of what I love!
Buy two pairs of
Essilor's best lenses
and get a $100 back instantly.
See more. Do more. Essilor
Narrator: In 2013,
Glafira Rosales'
astonishing 15-year art scam
appears to be over.
She got so enamored
of what she was doing
and thought that she was
so good at it
that she would absolutely
never get caught.
Narrator: But now if Rosales is
convicted on tax
and wire fraud charges,
she faces more than
three decades behind bars.
The magistrate judge
denied her bail.
And her being detained,
held without bail,
probably caused her
to think real hard
about what her options were
in this case.
Glafira Rosales admits
to passing off
fake paintings as real,
with the help of her boyfriend,
Jose Carlos Bergantiños Diaz,
and his brother, Jesus.
Hernandez:
One of the things that makes
a fraud like this successful
is a good false provenance.
And the Bergantiños Diaz
brothers were adept at that.
They would conduct research
in the historical record,
in books,
anything they could find
so that when the paintings were
passed off it was believable.
Narrator: Glafira also
names the artist forger,
an elderly Chinese immigrant
in Queens named Pei-Shen Qian.
For 15 years, Pei-Shen Qian
became Jackson Pollock,
Robert Motherwell,
Franz Kline, Mark Rothko,
and any a number of artists.
Narrator: In the 1970s,
Qian used to paint portraits
of Chairman Mao
for schools and factories
before immigrating
to the United States.
He didn't have much luck
as a serious artist in the U.S.
and resorted
to hustling portraits
on the sidewalks of Manhattan.
This is someone who
Jose Bergantiños Diaz
and Glafira Rosales found
just painting in New York City
one day,
and they challenged him.
They explained how buyers
are simply looking for works
in the manner of
Abstract Expressionist masters.
They asked him to paint
in the style
of Rothko or Pollock
to see if he could do it.
And not only could he do it.
He could do it well.
Narrator: For the next 15 years,
in his modest studio in Queens,
Pei-Shen Qian creates dozens
of look-alikes.
This is a painting created
by Pei-Shen Qian, the forger.
It's a painting that's supposed
to look like Mark Rothko.
It had the right color scheme,
had the right style
for a Mark Rothko.
You can see if you get close,
you can see some of
the brush strokes --
all consistent with
the way Rothko painted.
Narrator: But it takes more than
technique to fool savvy dealers.
According to Rosales,
that's where Jose stepped in
to add his expertise.
Hernandez: You needed
older canvas for a painting
that's supposed to be
60 years old.
So, they would go
to flea markets
and look for paintings
that were the right age
and frames that were
of the right age.
Narrator: Once Pei-Shen
finished a painting,
Bergantiños added
another touch of age.
Hernandez: He would do things
like empty
the vacuum cleaner dustbin
into the paintings
so that dust
and dirt would get into
the crevices of the painting
as you would expect to find
in an older painting.
And he would stain the canvases
with tea bags
and do other things to them to
give them the appearance of age.
Narrator: Lastly, Bergantiños
forges a signature.
You can see, it's white paint
that he used to paint
the actual words,
but when you get close,
you can see a brown tint to it,
and it looks old
to the naked eye.
But when you actually test it,
the brown is not
from grime or age.
It's, like, a varnish on top
to make the white
not so brilliant.
Narrator: But in some cases,
the red flags
where remarkably apparent.
Like, if anyone had bothered
to look closer at this Pollock
that hung on Ann Freedman's wall
for decades.
The signature for this work
is down here,
in the lower right corner.
You can see the forger
didn't spell Pollock correctly.
It appears that
he left out a "C."
Narrator: Investigators
aren't sure
whether Pei-Shen Qian is on
to the scam from the beginning,
but it's clear
he eventually caught on.
As a matter of fact, there came
a time where he learned
how much the paintings
were being sold for,
and he negotiated a raise.
IRS agent Eric Jonke determines
that Pei-Shen Qian
gets paid
a few thousand dollars each
for his imitations of top
Abstract Expressionists.
Jonke: Mr. Bergantiños
was paying him
$3,000 to $8,000 per painting,
which is peanuts compared
to what Miss Rosales
was initially selling them for.
She's selling them
for hundreds of thousands
to millions of dollars.
Narrator: In September 2013,
Glafira Rosales pleads guilty
in court to wire fraud,
money laundering,
and tax evasion.
By the time Glafira confesses,
Pei-Shen Qian has fled
back to China.
If fame and fortune was
what he was hoping for,
then perhaps he is a success.
Nikas: His works were
in prominent museums.
They sold for tens of millions
of dollars in the aggregate.
He was a famous artist,
but not for who he was,
but who he was pretending to be.
Narrator: Jose Carlos
Bergantiños Diaz
and his brother have
taken refuge in Spain.
In 2016, Spanish courts rule
against extraditing
60-year-old Diaz.
He and his brother still
face charges in the U.S.
Here in the States,
Glafira Rosales is left
holding the bag.
She got nine months
of home detention,
and she's got some
supervised released time
and she got restitution
and forfeiture
to the tune
of about $81 million.
Narrator: In her defense,
attorneys argued that
Glafira's boyfriend
put her up to the scheme.
He was the one who had
found the art forger,
who then supplied Glafira
Rosales with the paintings.
A string of civil cases
have been filed
against Knoedler & Company,
art dealers Ann Freedman
and Julian Weissman,
and others taken in by Rosales.
No criminal charges were
filed against them.
This is so egregious
that there are people
who will go to their grave
saying, "Ann Freedman knew.
The Knoedler Gallery knew.
Julian Weissman knew.
How could they not know?"
Because they themselves
have never been on that end,
and they don't realize
what it means to be
the victim of a con artist.
Nikas: Glafira Rosales
really embedded herself
in the art world
in a careful way
that allowed Knoedler Gallery
to look at the situation
and say,
"This is convincing to us."
Narrator: Julian Weissman
declined to comment
for "American Greed."
To date, most of the lawsuits
have been settled out of court.
The defendants have denied
any wrongdoing.
Art and jewelry are
the last sort of bastions