>>> LOOK AT THE TIME I'VE GONE
LONG.
SO I'M OUT OF HERE.
TAKE IT AWAY, KENDIS.
>> YOU CAN HANG OUT AND DO THE
NEXT TWO HOURS IF YOU'D LIKE.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>>> WELCOME, EVERYBODY.
I'M KENDIS GIBSON WITH A VERY
BUSY NEWS HOUR AHEAD OF US.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS SOUTH FLORIDA
ARRIVING FOR DAY 172nd OF HIS
GOLF COURSES.
HIS FORMER CAMPAIGN CHAIRMAN IS
SPENDING TODAY AT HIS DONE FOR
MUCH OF THE LAST NINE MONTHS,
LOCKED UP.
PAUL MANAFORT'S RECKONING COULD
COME NEXT WEEK WHEN HE FACES A
MAXIMUM SENTENCE OF TEN YEARS IN
PRISON IN HIS D.C. CASE AFTER
PLEADING GUILTY TO CONSPIRING TO
OBSTRUCT JUSTICE AND DEFRAUDING
THE GOVERNMENT.
STILL THERE IS OUTRAGE, HOWEVER,
OVER MANAFORT'S SHOCKINGLY
LENIENT SENTENCE OF 47 MONTHS IN
PRISON FOR BANK AND TAX FRAUD,
WELL BELOW THE FEDERAL
GUIDELINES RANGE OF 19 TO 24
YEARS.
THE VIRGINIA JUDGE IN THE CASE
CALLING THE SPECIAL COUNSEL'S
GUIDELINES EXCESSIVE AND TOTALLY
OUT OF WHACK.
WELL, HERE'S THE PRESIDENT ON
THE SENTENCING.
>> I FEEL VERY BADLY FOR PAUL
MANAFORT.
I THINK IT'S BEEN A VERY, VERY
TOUGH TIME FOR HIM, BUT IF YOU
NOTICE, BOTH HIS LAWYER, A
HIGHLY RESPECTED MAN AND A VERY
HIGHLY RESPECTED JUDGE, THE
JUDGE, SAID THERE WAS NO
COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA.
>> MIKE VIQUEIRA IS JOINING US
AT THE WHITE HOUSE FOLLOWING THE
DEVELOPMENT AND, MIKE, IT SEEMED
AS IF THE PRESIDENT LOOKED AS IF
SOME SORT OF VINDICATION, THE
LENIENT SENTENCING FOR MANAFORT?
>> Reporter: WELL, IN A SENSE,
BUT THE PRESIDENT MISREPRESENTED
WHAT THE JUDGE SAID.
THE JUDGE SAID THAT PAUL
MANAFORT WAS NOT BEFORE HIS
COURT FOR THE PURPOSE OF
INVESTIGATING COLLUSION WITH
RUSSIA OR RUSSIAN INTERFERENCE
IN THE U.S. ELECTION, RATHER HE
WAS BEING SENTENCED FOR BANK
FRAUD AS WELL AS TAX EVASION AND
YOU'RE RIGHT TO POINT OUT,
KENDIS, THAT NEXT WEDNESDAY
COMES ANOTHER RECKONING FOR PAUL
MANAFORT WHERE HE APPEARS AT A
DIFFERENT FEDERAL COURT JUST
DOWN THE STREET HERE AT THE FOOT
OF CAPITOL HILL IN THE FEDERAL
COURTROOM OF JUDGE AMY BIRMEN
JACKSON WHO IS SENTENCING HIM ON
SEPARATE CHARGES INVOLVING THE
ILLEGAL LOBBYING THAT HE HAS
DONE FOR THE -- FOR UKRAINE OVER
THE YEARS.
HE COULD GET UP TO TEN YEARS FOR
THAT AS WELL, ALTHOUGH THE
SENTENCES COULD RUN
CONCURRENTLY.
IN THE VIRGINIA CASE IN THE
SENTENCING JUST THE OTHER NIGHT
ON THURSDAY NIGHT, HE DOES GET
CREDIT FOR TIME SERVED, SO THAT
FOUR YEARS HE WAS SENTENCED FOR
WELL UNDER THE GUIDELINES THAT
COULD HAVE HAD HIM LOCKED UP FOR
AS MUCH AS 24 YEARS IS ALREADY
NINE MONTHS TO THE GOOD FOR PAUL
MANAFORT.
THE PRESIDENT EMBRACING WHAT THE
JUDGE SAID IN THAT THE JUDGE
TELLING MANAFORT THAT HE'S
LARGELY A BLAMELESS LIFE TILL
NOW.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WOULD TAKE ISSUE
WITH THAT AND A LOT OF PEOPLE
WOULD TAKE ISSUE WITH THE JUDGE
AND THE PERSONALITY THAT HE
INJECTED INTO THE COURTROOM IN
SOME OF HIS OWN PERSONAL VIEWS
OVER THE COURSE OF THAT TRIAL
AND YET PAUL MANAFORT WHO IS NOW
FRAIL, IN A WHEELCHAIR,
SUFFERING FROM GOUT IN A GREEN
PRISON JUMP SUIT WITH THE WORD
ALEXANDRIA INMATE STEN SILD ON
THE BACK WAS A FIGURE IN
DECLINING HEALTH APPARENTLY
AGAIN FACES THE MUSIC ON
WEDNESDAY WHEN HE APPEARS IN
FEDERAL COURT FOR HIS SENTENCING
IN A SECOND CASE BROUGHT BY THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL, KENDIS.
>> IT SEEMS THAT WITH SOME NEW
LAWS THAT HE COULD ACTUALLY END
UP JUST SPENDING 22 MONTHS
BEHIND LAWS AFTER ALL OF THIS.
OUR MIKE VIQUEIRA THERE AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
>>> FOR MORE ON THIS LET'S BRING
IN OUR PANEL, SOPHIA NELSON AND
GLENN KIRCHNER, AN MGS LEGAL
ANALYST, ANN GAREN, WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT AT "THE WASHINGTON
POST" AND CHARLIE SAVAGE, MSNBC
CONTRIBUTOR.
WARM WELCOME TO ALL OF YOU.
THANK YOU ALL FOR BEING HERE
WITH US.
GLENN, LET'S START WITH YOU.
WAS THIS AN INJUSTICE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I HEARD IN YOUR LEAD-IN, KENDIS,
THAT SOME PEOPLE WERE SAYING
THAT MUELLER'S GUIDELINES WERE
UNFAIR.
THESE ARE NOT MUELLER'S
GUIDELINES.
THERE IS A GUIDELINE COMMISSION
THAT CAME UP WITH THESE
GUIDELINES, A LOT OF DEEP
THINKERS, FORMER LAWYERS AND
FORMER JUDGES AND SO WHAT THEY
DID WAS THEY SAID, OKAY, FOR
THIS KIND OF OFFENDER, PAUL
MANAFORT AND FOR THESE KIND OF
OFFENSES, WHAT IS AN APPROPRIATE
GUIDELINE RANGE?
THAT'S NOT MUELLER SPECIFIC.
THAT'S EVERY FEDERAL COURT IN
THE COUNTRY AND A GUIDELINE
RANGE FOR THIS OFFENDER AND
THESE CRIMES CAME OUT TO BE 19.5
TO 24 YEARS.
NOW THERE ARE WAYS THAT JUDGES
CAN GO BELOW THAT, ONE WAY IS IF
SOMEBODY APOLOGIZES AND TAKES
RESPONSIBILITY FOR WHAT HE DID.
THE JUDGE SAID HE DIDN'T DO
THAT.
ANOTHER WAY IS IF YOU PROVIDE
SUBSTANTIAL ASSISTANCE TO THE
PROSECUTORS.
MANAFORT DIDN'T DO THAT.
IN FACT, HE LIED TO THE
PROSECUTORS UNDER THE GUISE OF
COOPERATING.
THERE WAS NO LAWFUL BASIS FOR
THE JUDGE TO DEPART DOWNWARD THE
WAY HE DID.
IT DOESN'T MAKE IT AN ILLEGAL
SENTENCE, BUT IT COULDN'T HAVE
BEEN A MORE UNJUST SENTENCE.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS.
THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE WHO
ARE BEHIND BARS FOR DOING A LOT
LESS.
I DO RECALL ONE WOMAN IN TEXAS
WHO GOT FIVE YEARS --
>> FOR TRYING TO VOTE.
>> VOTING ILLEGALLY.
WHAT DOES THIS SAY TO THE PUBLIC
ABOUT THE CRIMINAL JUSTICE
SYSTEM?
>> FIRST OF ALL, WE HAVE TO DEAL
WITH THE ISSUE OF PRIVILEGE.
WHITE COLLAR CRIMINALS HAVE
ALWAYS BEEN GIVEN PRIVILEGE IN
THE CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM.
THE SENTENCING GUIDELINES ARE
EXACTLY AS YOU SAY, THEY ARE
THERE FOR A REASON BECAUSE THEY
WANT YOU TO STAY WITHIN THOSE
GUIDELINES.
JUDGES ALWAYS HAVE DISCRETION,
BUT IN THIS ISSUE OF PAUL
MANAFORT, HERE'S A MAN THAT HAD
SIX PASSPORTS, IS ALLEGED TO
HAVE DONE ALL KIND OF THINGS
WITH RESPECT TO FOREIGN
GOVERNMENTS, NOT IN THE BEST
INTEREST PROBABLY OF THE UNITED
STATES IN MANY WAYS.
HERE'S A GUY THAT I DON'T FEEL
LIKE RUSSIAN COLLUSION HAS OR
HASN'T BEEN PROVEN YET BECAUSE
MUELLER HASN'T, YOU KNOW, ISSUED
HIS REPORT.
THE POINT IS THIS, HOWEVER,
LEAVE IT TO JUDGE JACKSON.
I BELIEVE SHE'S GOING TO STEP IN
AND IT'S GOING TO TAKE A WOMAN
TO CLEAN UP THIS MESS AND SHE'S
PRETTY TOUGH.
YOU SAW HOW SHE DEALT WITH ROGER
STONE.
I THINK SHE'S GOING TO RECTIFY
THIS, NOT BECAUSE SHE'S ON A
POLICY RANT OR SOME SOCIAL
JUSTICE RANT BUT BECAUSE SHE
GETS THE NEXT SHOT AT THIS.
>> AMY JACKSON THERE IN D.C.
WILL BE TAKING UP THE MANAFORT
CASE ON WEDNESDAY.
WE'LL BE TAKING UP THAT GAG
ORDER AGAINST ROGER STONE ON
MONDAY.
MANY PEOPLE ARE SAYING THAT THE
MUELLER TEAM TOOK AN "L" HERE,
THAT THEY TOOK THE LOSS.
>> THE MUELLER TEAM HAS A BYE
THAT THIS IS NOT THEIR CASE.
THEY HANDED OFF A FAIR AMOUNT OF
THE, YOU KNOW, CRIMINAL SIDE OF
THIS TO FEDERAL JUDGES AND THEY,
YOU KNOW -- THEY GAVE -- THERE
WAS A BROAD MANDATE TO PROSECUTE
MANAFORT ON THINGS THAT WERE
VERY DIFFERENT THAN THE MANDATE
TO LOOK INTO RUSSIA AND ALLEGED
COLLUSION AND SO FORTH, SO IF
YOU -- IF YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT
THE MUELLER CASE IN TERMS OF ARE
THEY GOING TO BE ABLE TO PIN
SOMETHING ON THE PRESIDENT, THE
MANAFORT CASE WAS ALWAYS SORT OF
OFF TO ONE SIDE.
WE DON'T KNOW YET AND WE DIDN'T
LEARN MUCH, FRANKLY, IN THE
COURSE OF THE MANAFORT
PROCEEDINGS ABOUT WHAT ALL OF
THAT SEPARATE LINE OF INQUIRY
WAS GOING TO BE, THE MANAFORT
CASE WAS LARGELY ABOUT THINGS
THAT MANAFORT DID BEFORE HE EVER
WENT TO WORK FOR DONALD TRUMP
AND SO IT'S SORT OF -- YOU HAVE
TO LOOK AT IT AS ITS OWN ANIMAL.
>> JUSTICE WILL COME BACK FOR
PAUL MANAFORT AS FAR AS MUELLER
IS CONCERNED.
CHARLIE, THERE'S AN INTERESTING
MESSAGE FROM PAUL MANAFORT'S
LAWYER THAT HE SAID AFTER THE
SENTENCING.
LISTEN.
>> I THINK MOST IMPORTANTLY WHAT
YOU SAW TODAY IS THE SAME THING
THAT WE HAD SAID FROM DAY ONE,
THERE IS ABSOLUTELY NO EVIDENCE
THAT PAUL MANAFORT WAS INVOLVED
WITH ANY COLLUSION WITH ANY
GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL FROM RUSSIA.
>> INTERESTING TALKING POINT.
SOUNDED SIMILAR TO WHAT THE
PRESIDENT SAID JUST ABOUT 12 OR
24 HOURS LATER.
WAS THIS A DELIBERATE APPEAL FOR
A PARDON FROM THE PRESIDENT?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON
INSIDE OF HIS HEAD.
ONE THING THAT WAS INTERESTING
ABOUT IT, THE WORD GOVERNMENT
OFFICIAL, BECAUSE ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT THE MANAFORT TRIAL
DID BRING TO LIGHT THAT HE
DURING THE CAMPAIGN WHILE
WORKING FOR DONALD TRUMP HAD
SHARED INTERNAL POLLING DATA
WITH KONSTANTIN KILIMNIK, THAT
RUSSIAN BUSINESSMAN THAT THE
GOVERNMENT SAYS HAS LINKS TO THE
RUSSIAN GRU INTELLIGENCE AGENCY
THAT HAD HACKED THE DEMOCRATIC
EMAILS.
I DON'T KNOW IF THAT WAS --
AMOUNTS TO COLLUSION BUT IT WAS
SOME KIND OF CONSPIRACY ACTION.
THE OTHER THING TO PAY ATTENTION
TO HERE, OF COURSE, IS NOT ONLY
DOES JUDGE JACKSON HAVE THE
OPPORTUNITY TO SENTENCE HIM TO
UP TO TEN YEARS THAT WOULD RUN
AFTER THESE 47 MONTHS, IF SHE
WANTS TO, BUT HE HAS ALREADY
AGREED TO FORFEIT SOMETHING LIKE
$46 MILLION IN ASSETS UNRELATED
TO THE JAIL TIME HE'S GOING TO
RECEIVE HERE.
THAT PENALTY IS ANOTHER GIGANTIC
PIECE OF DISCIPLINE THAT SHOULD
BE PART OF THE DISCUSSION OF
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO HIM.
>> SO YOU'LL HAVE MANAFORT IN
FRONT OF AMY JACKSON.
LET ME ASK YOU THIS BECAUSE YOU
TWEETED THIS.
DON'T DESPAIR AT TODAY'S
HORRIFIC INJUSTICE AT THE HANDS
OF JUDGE ELLIS, THE CONSPIRACY
INDICTMENT IS COMING, IN MY
OPINION.
DON'T CONFUSE MUELLER'S SILENCE
ON THE CONSPIRACY FRONT WITH
LACK OF EVIDENCE ON CONSPIRACY.
JUSTICE IS COMING BACK.
>> WHAT I MEAN BY THAT IS, AFTER
SPENDING 30 YEARS AS A
PROSECUTOR, THE EVIDENCE I HAVE
SEEN EVEN IN THE PUBLIC
REPORTING TELLS ME THAT THERE
WAS A CONSPIRACY BETWEEN THE
CAMPAIGN AND RUSSIA.
WE'VE SEEN IT OVER AND OVER
AGAIN, THEN THERE WERE ALL SORTS
OF ACTS UNDERTAKEN THAT
OBSTRUCTED JUSTICE, THAT TRIED
TO PREVENT THE EVIDENCE OF THAT
CONSPIRACY COMING TO LIGHT.
SO EVERYBODY HAS CONFUSED
MUELLER'S SILENCE ON THE
QUESTION OF CONSPIRACY AND
COLLUSION WITH AN ABSENCE OF
EVIDENCE OF CONSPIRACY.
>> YOU THINK THE COLLUSION BOMB
IS STILL COMING.
>> THE COLLUSION BOMB IS COMING
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
MUELLER IS SO STRATEGIC IN WHAT
HE'S DOING, I DON'T THINK HE
WANTED TO TIP HIS HAND ON
COLLUSION.
I DON'T THINK HE WANTED TO, FOR
EXAMPLE, INDICT ONE OF THE
PRESIDENT'S CHILDREN FOR SOME OF
THE CRIMES THEY COMMITTED
BECAUSE THAT MAY HAVE RESULTED
IN TRUMP TRYING TO SHUT THINGS
DOWN.
>> I AGREE WITH HIM, BUT AT THE
VERY BEST CASE SCENARIO FOR THE
PRESIDENT, IT WAS RECKLESS
ABJECT GREED, GIVE ME SOME WORDS
HERE FOR WHAT THEY TRIED TO DO
BECAUSE BUSINESS FOR HIM AND
CRIMINALITY PERHAPS, ET CETERA,
I THINK THEY ALL MERGE TOGETHER.
I DON'T THINK THEY THINK ALONG
THOSE LINES AND KUSHNER, LET US
NOT FORGET, NOT TO IMPUGN
PEOPLE'S PARENTS, HIS FATHER WAS
CONVICT THE BY CHRIS CHRISTIE
AND IN MOST WHITE HOUSES AND IN
MOST GOVERNMENTS, SOMEONE WHO
HAD A FAMILY HISTORY WITH A
FELON, IT DOESN'T MEAN YOU'RE
BAD BECAUSE YOU HAVE A FELON IN
THE FAMILY, BUT SOME OF THIS
BEHAVIOR WITH MBS ON JARED
KUSHNER'S PART IS JUST
PROBLEMATIC.
THESE GUYS DON'T CARE ABOUT LAW,
JUSTICE, INTEGRITY.
THEY DON'T.
>> THEY DON'T.
>> ROGER STONE GOING TO JAIL ON
MONDAY?
>> I THINK --
>> IT'S A QUICK YES OR NO.
>> I THINK NOT.
>> I DO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SOPHIA AND GLENN, STICK AROUND.
ANNA AND CHARLIE, THANK YOU SO
MUCH.
>>> SO SHOW ME THE MONEY.
WHILE PRESIDENT TRUMP IS IN
MAR-A-LAGO COLLECTING CASH,
BERNIE SANDERS IS IN THE HAWKEYE
STATE TRYING TO COLLECT
SUPPORTERS.
>>> PLUS, ALMOST BUT NOT QUITE,
HOW CLOSE JOE BIDEN IS TO MAKING
A DECISION ABOUT 2020.
If you have postmenopausal
osteoporosis
and a high risk for fracture
now might not be the best time
to ask yourself
are my bones strong?
Life is full of make-or-break
moments.
That's why it's so important
to help reduce your risk of
fracture with Prolia®.
Only Prolia® is proven to help
strengthen
and protect bones from fracture
with 1 shot every 6 months.
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take
XGEVA®.
Serious allergic reactions,
like low blood pressure; trouble
breathing;
throat tightness; face, lip, or
tongue swelling;
rash; itching; or hives have
happened.
Tell your doctor about dental
problems
as severe jaw bone problems may
happen
or new or unusual pain in your
hip groin, or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone fractures
have occurred.
Speak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects,
like low blood calcium, serious
infections,
which could need
hospitalization, skin problems,
and severe bone, joint, or
muscle pain.
Are you ready?
Ask your doctor how Prolia® can
help strengthen your bones.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
We're the Tenney's
and we're USAA members for life.
Call USAA to start saving
on insurance today.
This is not a bed...
it's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed, from $999...
senses your movement and
automatically adjusts
on each side to keep
you both comfortable.
And snoring?
How smart is that?
Smarter sleep.
So you can come out swinging,
maintain your inner
focus, and wake up rested
and ready for anything.
Only at a Sleep Number store,
save $500 on select Sleep
Number 360 smart beds.
Plus, free premium
delivery and setup.
Ends March 17th.
With tough food, your dentures
may slip and fall.
Fixodent Ultra-Max Hold
gives you the strongest hold
ever
to lock your dentures.
So now you can eat tough food
without worry.
Fixodent and forget it.
>>> SOME BIG CROWDS ARE SHOWING
UP FOR AN ALREADY CROWDED FIELD.
THE BEAT TRUMP FERVOR AT "NEW
YORK TIMES" IS CALLING IT IS
ENERGIZING DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES
TO RUN AND VOTERS TO TURN OUT AT
MASSIVE EVENTS ALL ACROSS THE
COUNTRY AS THE TIMES WRITES,
POWERED BY AN ALMOST DESPERATE
YEARNING TO OUST PRESIDENT TRUMP
AND GALVANIZED BY THE MOST
DIVERSE FIELD IN PRESIDENTIAL
PRIMARY HISTORY, DEMOCRATS ARE
PACKING INTO GYMS AND CHURCHES
TO HEAR THE CANDIDATES SPEAK.
EVEN IF THEY ARE FAR FROM
COMMITTED TO SUPPORTING THE
CANDIDATE, THEY ARE SHOWING UP
TO SEE.
LET'S BRING IN J SHAQUILLE
BREWSTER.
WHAT DID IT LOOK LIKE TODAY IN
DES MOINES?
>> Reporter: WELL, IT WASN'T THE
12 OR 13,000 THAT WE SAW IN
NEW YORK AND CHICAGO, CAMPAIGN
SAYS IT WAS ABOUT 1,300 PEOPLE
THAT SHOWED UP HERE IN DES
MOINES WHICH IS CONSISTENT WITH
THE OTHER EVENTS THAT WE'VE SEEN
FROM BERNIE SANDERS DURING THIS
FIRST TRIP BACK TO IOWA AS AN
OFFICIAL 2020 PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATE AND I'VE BEEN TALKING
TO A LOT OF PEOPLE HERE AT THESE
RALLIES BEFORE THE EVENTS AND
THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO ARE 100%
WITH BERNIE SANDERS.
THERE'S OTHERS LIKE ASHLEY DOOR
WHO ARE STILL ON THE FENCE.
LISTEN TO WHAT SHE HAD TO SAY
EARLIER.
>> IN THE PAST I HAVEN'T BEEN
VERY INVOLVED POLITICALLY AND
THIS YEAR, I JUST WANT TO GET
OUT AND LEARN AS MUCH AS I CAN
ABOUT CANDIDATES.
I WANT TO LEARN ABOUT WHAT THEY
STAND FOR, WHAT ARE THE ISSUES
THEY'RE REALLY PULLING FOR.
RIGHT NOW IN OUR COUNTRY WE'RE
IN A SPOT WHERE IT'S EITHER WE
FIGURE IT OUT OR WE KEEP GOING
IN THE DIRECTION THAT WE'RE
GOING.
>> Reporter: AND ASHLEY TEXTED
ME AFTERWARDS SAYING THAT SHE
FEELS LIKE BERNIE IS THE
PEOPLE'S CANDIDATE, SHE CAME IN
UNDECIDED BUT IS NOW LEANING
MORE TO SANDERS.
SANDERS IS GOING TO
NEW HAMPSHIRE LATER, THEN HE'S
GOING TO SOUTH CAROLINA LATER IN
THE WEEK AND HE REALLY IS
COMMITTED TO FIGHTING THIS
FIGHT.
HE SAYS THAT UNLIKE 2016, WHEN
HE WAS A FRINGE CANDIDATE WHO
JUST CAME ABOUT AND STARTED AT
3% IN THE POLL, THIS TIME AROUND
HE HAS THE ISSUES ON HIS SIDE
AND HE'S HAPPY TO SEE MUCH OF
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY BACKING HIS
SIDE.
HE ACTUALLY MADE A NOTE EARLIER
TODAY TO SAY THAT HE DOES EXPECT
TO WIN BUT IF HE DOES NOT WIN,
HE DOES PLAN ON SUPPORTING THE
DEMOCRATIC NOMINEE.
THAT WAS SOMETHING THAT'S
NOTABLE BECAUSE HE'S RECEIVED
CRITICISM FROM SOME WHO SAY THAT
HE DIDN'T COME OUT FOR SECRETARY
CLINTON AFTER HE LOST IN 2016,
THAT HE DIDN'T COME OUT FOR HER
FORCEFULLY OR QUICKLY ENOUGH.
IT'S INTERESTING TO SEE THAT
CHANGE IN TONE.
BACK TO YOU.
>> IT CERTAINLY HAS BEEN THE RUB
ON HIM FOR THE LAST TWO YEARS OR
SO.
I DO WANT TO ASK YOU THIS, AT
LEAST WITH ASHLEY AND IN THAT
PARTICULAR SHOT, THEY APPEAR TO
BE FAIRLY YOUNG AND THAT WAS
BERNIE'S BIG THING ABOUT TWO
YEARS AGO, GETTING THE YOUNG
PEOPLE.
WHAT WAS THE MAKE-UP LIKE THERE
IN DES MOINES?
>> Reporter: A LOT OF YOUNG
PEOPLE, HE WAS ON A COLLEGE
CAMPUS YESTERDAY IN IOWA CITY
AND HE MADE A POINT.
IT WAS ONE OF HIS APPLAUSE LINES
THAT BACK IN 2016 HE RECEIVED
MORE VOTES FROM YOUNG PEOPLE
THAN PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
SECRETARY HILLARY CLINTON
COMBINED, SO HE LIKES THE FACT
THAT HE HAS THE SUPPORT OF THE
YOUNG PEOPLE.
THERE ARE PLENTY OF PEOPLE I'VE
MET OVER THESE PAST COUPLE OF
DAYS WHO WEREN'T ABLE TO VOTE IN
2016.
THEY VOLUNTEERED, THEY MADE
CALLS FOR HIM BUT THEY WEREN'T
ABLE TO CAST A BALLOT.
IT IS NOW THEIR TIME TO VOTE AND
THEY PLAN ON COMING OUT AND
SUPPORTING HIM, SENATOR SANDERS
SAYS THAT HE IS OVER 7,000
PEOPLE WHO ALREADY SIGNED UP
JUST HERE IN IOWA TO HELP
VOLUNTEER FOR HIM.
HE'S SERIOUS ABOUT GETTING THAT
SUPPORT.
>> I GUESS THAT YOUNG SUPPORT IS
RELATIVE WHEN YOU'RE 77 YEARS
OLD, OF COURSE, THOSE NUMBERS
MAKE SENSE TO YOU.
SHAQUILLE BREWSTER, THANK YOU.
>>> REPUBLICAN STRATEGIST AND
AUTHOR, NOELLE.
>>> I WANT TO PLAY SOUND FROM
BERNIE SANDERS TODAY.
JUST MOMENTS AGO, GET YOUR TAKE
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
♪♪
>> I HOPE VERY MUCH TWO THINGS,
NUMBER ONE, THAT THE NATURE OF
OUR CAMPAIGN IS NOT BELITTLING
PEOPLE, IT'S NOT OPPOSITION
RESEARCH, IT'S NOT ATTACKING
OTHER PEOPLE, BUT IS A SERIOUS
DISCUSSION ABOUT THE IMPORTANT
ISSUES FACING THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE.
IF WE DO NOT WIN, I WILL
STRONGLY SUPPORT THE DEMOCRATIC
NOMINEE AND HOPE THAT -- AND
HOPE AND BELIEVE THAT OTHERS
FEEL EXACTLY THE SAME WAY.
DONALD TRUMP MUST BE DEFEATED.
>> ED, DO YOU HEAR RIGHT THERE
THE BIGGEST APPLAUSE LINE RIGHT
NOW, IT IS ABOUT BEATING TRUMP.
WHAT DO YOU THINK WHEN YOU HEAR
THAT MESSAGE THERE FROM SANDERS?
>> WELL, OBVIOUSLY THAT'S THE
NUMBER ONE PRIORITY FOR THE
ENTIRE PARTY AND PROBABLY FOR
MUCH OF THE NATION.
2016 LEFT PEOPLE VERY
DISAPPOINTED AND ANGRY AND
THANKFULLY THAT ENERGY WAS MOVED
INTO ACTUALLY TAKING THE HOUSE
BACK IN 2018.
I THINK WE'RE SEEING VERY EARLY
ON AN EVEN MORE INTENSE ENERGY,
POSITIVE ENERGY TO TAKE THE
HOUSE BACK.
ON THE FLIP SIDE -- TO TAKE THE
WHITE HOUSE BACK.
THE FLIP SIDE WHEN I LISTEN TO
BERNIE IS SORT OF A, HERE WE GO
AGAIN.
YOU SHOULD NOT HAVE TO SAY, IF I
LOSE I'M GOING TO BACK UP THE
DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATE.
THE FACT THAT YOU HAVE TO SAY
THAT IS AN INDICATION OF A PRIOR
PROBLEM AND AS SOMEONE WHO
WORKED FOR HILLARY CLINTON BOTH
IN 2008 WHEN SHE LOST TO BARACK
OBAMA AND THEN 2016 WHEN SHE
BEAT BERNIE SANDERS, THERE
REALLY WAS A DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
THE TWO.
I REMEMBER SOMEONE ADDING UP
EVERYTHING THAT HILLARY DID FOR
PRESIDENT OBAMA AND SHE DID MORE
EVENTS AND RAISED MORE MONEY FOR
HIM THAN SARAH PALIN DID FOR
JOHN McCAIN AND BERNIE SANDERS,
IF HE DOESN'T WIN, HE NEEDS TO
DO THAT SAME THING AND INSTEAD,
WE ARE TAKING PLEDGES ABOUT
WHETHER YOU WILL REMAIN A
DEMOCRAT.
THAT'S A PROBLEM.
>> MANY PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
POINTING OUT THAT HE IS AN
INDEPENDENT.
HE'S SAYING HE'S A PROUD
DEMOCRAT AT LEAST IN THIS RACE.
NOELLE, MY COLLEAGUES PUBLISHED
AN INTERESTING PIECE DISCUSSING
SANDERS' CHALLENGES.
TAKE A LOOK.
THE FIRST CHALLENGE THEY SAY IS,
CAN HE COMPETE IN A MUCH MORE
CROWDED LIBERAL/PROGRESSIVE LANE
THAN HE ENCOUNTERED IN 2016?
HE'S GOT COMPANY FROM THE
PROGRESSIVE, INCLUDING ELIZABETH
WARREN TO THE LIKES OF KAMALA
HARRIS, CORY BOOKER, KRISTIN
JILL BRAND WHO ARE ALL RUNNING
UNDER THE MEDICARE FOR ALL
BANNER, WHERE DOES BERNIE RUN?
WHAT IS HIS LANE?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, BERNIE'S
GOING TO HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
EXACTLY WHAT HE'S DOING AND I
THINK THAT HE'S ALREADY GOTTEN A
GOOD GRIP ON THAT BY COMING OUT
AND SAYING THAT HE'S PRETTY MUCH
STATED, YOU KNOW, THE POLICY
THAT EVERYBODY ELSE IS GOING
AROUND AND THAT'S ONE OF THE
THINGS IF YOU ARE IN THE BERNIE
CAMP, YOU CAN SIT BACK AND GO,
PRETTY MUCH I TOLD YOU SO.
THIS IS THE MESSAGE.
THIS IS THE NARRATIVE THAT'S
REGISTERING AND THIS IS WHAT ALL
THE NEW NEW CANDIDATES THAT ARE
COMING FORTH ARE ALL PRETTY MUCH
MIMICKING SOME OF THE ORIGINAL
POINTS THAT BERNIE SANDERS MADE,
SO OBVIOUSLY BERNIE SANDERS WHO
GAVE HILLARY CLINTON A REAL RUN
FOR HER MONEY REALLY RESONATED
WITH NOT ONLY A LOT OF THE YOUNG
DONORS, BUT -- OR YOUNG VOTERS,
BUT ALSO WITH A LOT OF THE BASE
OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
LOOK AT SOME OF THE CONGRESSMEN
THAT HAVE BEEN ELECTED AND THESE
ARE VERY FAR LEFT LEANING
CANDIDATES THAT WON.
>> NOELLE, NOT TO -- I DON'T
THINK LOSING BY 4 MILLION VOTES
IS GIVING SOMEONE A RUN FOR
THEIR MONEY AND MOST OF THE
CANDIDATES WHO WON IN 2018 DID
SO ON A MORE MODERATE PLATFORM.
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT WHAT BERNIE
HAS DONE.
THE PROBLEM FOR BERNIE MIGHT BE
A DOUBLE-EDGED SWORD.
THE FACT THAT HE HAS BROUGHT THE
CONVERSATION TO THE ISSUES THAT
HE WANTS, HE NOW HAS CREATED A
SITUATION WHERE PEOPLE LIKE YOU
SAID HAVE OPTIONS.
THEY HAVE A LOT OF OPTIONS, AND
THE QUESTION IS WHETHER HE HAS
OVER THE LAST TWO YEARS MANAGED
TO BRING TOGETHER THE PEOPLE
THAT DIDN'T VOTE FOR HIM AND IT
DOES NOT SEEM LIKE HE'S BEEN
VERY GOOD AT THAT.
IT SEEMS LIKE TO SOME EXTENT HE
HAS SQUANDERED THE LAST TWO
YEARS.
>> HE HAS TOO MANY OPTIONS.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
>> THERE ARE MANY REPORTS THAT
HE'S PREPARING TO ANNOUNCE,
MICHAEL BLOOMBERG AND SHERROD
BROWN HAVE BOWED OUT, BUT HIS
LIKELY ENTRANCE SEEMS TO HAVE
BARELY CLEAR THE FIELD.
IT REMAINS WIDE-OPEN.
HOW DO YOU SEE HIM INFLUENCING
THE CHANGES AND THE CHANCES OF
OTHER DEMOCRATS RIGHT NOW?
>> I THINK IT'S GREAT THAT IT
DOESN'T CLEAR THE FIELD.
IT'S IMPORTANT THAT IF PEOPLE
WANT TO RUN, IF THEY THINK THEY
HAVE SOMETHING TO OFFER, THAT
THEY RUN.
JOE BIDEN OBVIOUSLY HAS THE
RESPECT AND ADMIRATION OF
MILLIONS OF DEMOCRATS, INCLUDING
MYSELF.
I THINK -- I GIVE VICE PRESIDENT
BIDEN A LOT OF CREDIT BECAUSE I
THINK HE'S BEING VERY THOUGHTFUL
AND METICULOUS ABOUT RUNNING OR
THE DECISION TO RUN BECAUSE HE
KNOWS THERE'S A GREAT CHANCE
THAT HE DOESN'T WIN AND I THINK
HE, YOU KNOW, MORE THAN
ANYTHING, DOESN'T WANT TO REGRET
NOT TAKING ANOTHER SHOT.
>> OKAY.
>> THE FLIP SIDE OF THAT, HE'S
BEEN IN PUBLIC SERVICE FOR 40
YEARS AND HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO
BASICALLY START FROM SCRATCH AND
EXPLAIN A LOT OF WHAT HE SAID
AND CONVINCE PEOPLE THAT HE
WOULD BE BETTER THAN KAMALA
HARRIS OR ELIZABETH WARREN.
>> AND 40 YEARS OF RECORD, A LOT
OF IT IS COMING UP OVER THE LAST
FEW WEEKS --
>> EXPERIENCE HAS BECOME A DIRTY
WORD NOW.
>> IT REALLY HAS.
OUR THANKS TO BOTH OF YOU.
IT'S 78 DEGREES WHERE YOU ARE
WITH A WIND CHILL OF LIKE 90.
TOUGH PROBLEMS.
>> NEXT TIME YOU HAVE TO FLY ME
TO FLORIDA TO DO WITH NOELLE IN
PERSON.
>> SOUNDS LIKE A DEAL.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
>>> PARDON PROBLEMS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS MICHAEL
COHEN DIRECTLY ASKED HIM FOR A
PARDON BUT HIS FORMER FIXER SAYS
IT'S JUST ANOTHER SET OF LIES.
IT'S A CASE OF HE SAID/HE SAID
NEXT.
Guys do whatever it takes to
deal with shave irritation.
So, we re-imagined the razor
with the new Gillette SkinGuard.
It has a unique guard
between the blades.
That's designed to reduce
irritation during the shave.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
Gillette.
I've always been amazed
by what's next.
And still going for my best,
even though I live with
a higher risk of stroke
due to Afib not caused by
a heart valve problem.
So if there's a better treatment
than warfarin...
I want that too.
ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS is proven
to reduce stroke risk
better than warfarin.
Plus has significantly less
major bleeding than warfarin.
ELIQUIS is FDA-approved
and has both.
What's next?
Reeling in a nice one.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS
unless your doctor tells you to,
as stopping increases your risk
of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS If you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily
and it may take longer than
usual for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden sign of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase your
bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor
about all planned medical
or dental procedures.
ELIQUIS, the number one
cardiologist-prescribed
blood thinner.
Ask your doctor if ELIQUIS
is what's next for you.
>>> SO RELATIONSHIP EXPERTS SAY
THERE ARE FIVE PHASES OF
BREAK-UPS, DENIAL, ANGER,
BARGAINING, DEPRESSION AND
ACCEPTANCE.
IT SEEMS LIKE PRESIDENT TRUMP
AND HIS FORMER FIXER ARE ADDING
RETALIATION TO THEIR BREAK-UP.
THE PRESIDENT GOING ALL CAPS,
TAKE A LOOK ON THE TWEET
BLASTING COHEN WITH, HE LIED AND
GOING ON TO SAY COHEN DIRECTLY
ASKED HIM FOR A PARDON.
SO MINUTES LATER, COHEN
RESPONDED BY CLAIMING, IT WAS
JUST ANOTHER SET OF LIES BY HIS
FORMER BOSS.
THE PARDON TALKS PRESUMABLY
HAPPENED BEFORE COHEN FLIPPED ON
TRUMP AND THEIR WAR OF WORDS IS
RAISING THE QUESTION, WHO
OBSTRUCTED JUSTICE OR PERJURED
FIRST?
JOINING ME RIGHT NOW IS CAROLINE
PALESI.
IT MAKES YOU FEEL LIKE YOU
MISSED THE DAYS WHEN PEOPLE
WOULD JUST GHOST EACH OTHER
AFTER THE RELATIONSHIP BREAK-UP.
LET ME START WITH YOU.
WITH JUST ONE HOUR BEFORE
SENDING OUT THAT TWEET THAT
TRUMP WAS STILL -- WAS SAYING
THAT HIS LAWYERS WERE WATCHING
EVERYTHING THAT WAS PLAYING OUT,
THAT THERE WERE DISCUSSIONS
BETWEEN HIS LAWYERS AND COHEN'S
LAWYERS AS WELL.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT WAS HAPPENING THERE?
>> IT LOOKS LIKE COHEN MAY HAVE
FUDGED A LITTLE BIT WHEN YOU
ASSIMILATE ALL THE REPORTING
WE'VE HEARD.
HE MAY HAVE FUDGED A LITTLE BIT
WHEN HE SAID HE NEVER ASKED FOR
A PARDON, AND, OF COURSE, HIS
OWN LAWYER CAME OUT AND SAID, HE
DID AUTHORIZE ME TO EXPLORE IT
WITH TRUMP'S LAWYERS.
BUT HERE'S THE BOTTOM LINE, WHEN
THE PRESIDENT SAYS IN A
ONE-ON-ONE CONVERSATION MICHAEL
COHEN ASKED ME FOR A PARDON,
OKAY, FINE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW YOU COULD CHARGE
MICHAEL COHEN WITH PERJURY IF HE
DID LIE TO CONGRESS?
THE PRESIDENT WOULD HAVE TO WALK
IN TO A GRAND JURY AND TESTIFY
THAT MICHAEL COHEN -- YOU THINK
HE'S GOING TO DO THAT?
HE WOULDN'T EVEN SIT DOWN FOR A
VOLUNTARY INTERVIEW WITH MUELLER
BECAUSE HE WAS SO SCARED AND HIS
LAWYERS WERE SO SCARED OF HIM
NOT BEING TRUTHFUL.
SO THIS IS MUCH ADO ABOUT
NOTHING.
THIS IS A COOPERATOR NOT BEING
100% STRAIGHT DURING HIS
COOPERATION.
WE SEE IT ALL THE TIME.
>> THE BIG QUESTION MANY
REPUBLICANS ARE WONDERING IS
WHETHER OR NOT COHEN COMMITTED
PERJURY ON FEBRUARY 27th WHEN HE
WAS THERE IN FRONT OF CONGRESS
AGAIN?
>> HOW DO WE EVER KNOW?
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
THIS IS A HE SAID/HE SAID.
WHETHER OR NOT HE ASKED FOR A
PARDON, AFTER THE FBI RAID IS
WHEN I SUSPECT THERE WAS REAL
FEAR IN COHEN CAMP.
HE AND TRUMP WERE STILL BOYS
THEN.
WAS IT A DIRECT -- YOU GOT TO
PARDON ME?
PROBABLY NOT.
WAS IT A LITTLE SLIPPERY?
PROBABLY SO.
THEY'RE BROMANCE IS OVER.
IT'S BAD.
I THINK ON THE BIGGER QUESTION
ON WHETHER HE PERJURED HIMSELF,
I AGREE WITH YOU, THAT UNLESS
TRUMP'S GOING TO GO UP TO
CONGRESS, WHICH HE'S NOT GOING
TO DO, WE'RE NOT GOING TO KNOW.
IT'S HIM AGAINST HIM.
>> MANY PEOPLE ARE WONDERING
WHETHER OR NOT TRUMP'S
STATEMENTS AND SOME OF HIS
TWEETS COULD BE CONSIDERED
WITNESS TAMPERING BECAUSE
MICHAEL COHEN IS STILL
COOPERATING WITH MANY
INVESTIGATIONS RIGHT NOW.
>> HE'S BEEN ACCUSED OF THAT
BEFORE.
A LOT OF HIS TWEETS WERE VERY
THREATENING.
HE THREATENED MICHAEL COHEN'S
FATHER-IN-LAW BEFORE THE FIRST
TIME HE WAS GOING IN TO TESTIFY.
THE BIGGER ISSUE IS THE
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE QUESTION
BECAUSE WE'RE ASKING -- WE'RE SO
FOCUSED ON THE PERJURY.
WHAT WAS THE UNDERLYING ISSUE?
IT WAS THE DANGLING OF A
POTENTIAL PARDON, WHETHER HE DID
IT OR DIDN'T.
THIS IS A BIGGER QUESTION THAT
GOES TO MANAFORT, FLYNN.
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THESE
DEFENDANTS AND WE KNOW FROM BILL
BARR'S TESTIMONY THAT HE
BELIEVES THAT A DANGLE OF A
PARDON COULD POTENTIALLY BE
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE, WHICH IS
ODD THAT HE WOULD BELIEVE THAT
BECAUSE HE ALSO WROTE THAT MEMO
SAYING THAT HE BELIEVED THAT
FIRING JOHN McCAIN COULDN'T BE
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
IT'S ANYBODY'S GAME AT THIS
POINT OF WHAT DOES AND DOESN'T
QUALIFY.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE PICKING
UP ON JUST THE FIRST FEW
PARAGRAPHS THERE BY BILL BARR
MORE THAN A YEAR AGO.
I WANT TO SWITCH GEARS NOW.
I SAW THE HEADLINE JUST A COUPLE
DAYS AGO.
MICHAEL COHEN IS SUING THE TRUMP
ORGANIZATION FOR NEARLY
$2 MILLION.
LAWSUIT THERE READING IN PART,
QUOTE, MR. COHEN HAS BEEN
ORDERED TO PAY OR FORFEIT
APPROXIMATELY $1.9 MILLION AS
PART OF HIS CRIMINAL SENTENCE
ARISING FROM CONDUCT UNDERTAKEN
BY MR. COHEN IN FURTHERANCE OF
AND AT THE BEHEFT OF THE TRUMP
ORGANIZATION AND ITS PRINCIPLES,
DIRECTORS AND OFFICERS.
INTERESTING OPTICS HERE.
>> TWO THOUGHTS, ONE YOU CANNOT
MAKE THIS UP.
I CONTINUE TO FEEL LIKE I'M IN
BIZARRO LAND THAT WE'RE HAVING
THIS OPEN CONVERSATION ABOUT A
SITTING PRESIDENT AND ALL THESE
ALLEGED ACTS OF CRIMINAL
INFLUENCE, TAMPERING.
MICHAEL COHEN WANTED LAWYER FEES
FROM TRUMP FOR A WHILE.
HE ASKED FOR THEM LIKE RIGHT
AROUND THE TIME OF THE RAID IF
I'M CORRECT AND I'M NOT
SURPRISED ABOUT THIS AT ALL
BECAUSE HE FEELS LIKE I DID
THESE THINGS ON BEHALF OF,
THEREFORE, I'M IN TROUBLE
BECAUSE OF YOU AND HE ALSO
IDENTIFIED THE PRESIDENT AS
INDIVIDUAL NUMBER ONE.
HE SAID THAT IN HIS TESTIMONY.
WE HAVEN'T BEEN TALKING ABOUT
THAT A WHOLE LOT.
WE SHOULD BE TALKING ABOUT THAT.
I'M NOT SURPRISED THAT HE'S
ASKING FOR THE FEES.
HE'S NOT GOING TO GET THEM,
PROBABLY, BUT HE'S ASKING.
>> SDNY IS LOOKING INTO
INDIVIDUAL NUMBER ONE QUITE A
BIT THERE.
>> YES.
>> THIS IS A REALLY BUSY MONTH.
HIS TESTIMONY BEFORE THE HOUSE
JANS COMMITTEE IS NOW POSTPONED
UNTIL MARCH 27th.
YOU SEE THERE.
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING TO HEAR
FROM HIM?
>> THIS GUY HAS BEEN ON THE
PERIPHERY THIS WHOLE TIME
LURKING IN THE BACKGROUND AND HE
REALLY CAME INTO THE SPOTLIGHT
DURING MICHAEL COHEN'S TESTIMONY
WHICH HE JUST GAVE.
MICHAEL COHEN STATED THAT FELIX
SEDER NOT ONLY DID EVAN OFFICE
AT THE TRUMP OFFICE BUT IT WAS
ON DONALD TRUMP'S FLOOR.
THE ISSUE IS HOW INVOLVED IS HE
IN THE TRUMP TOWER/MOSCOW
PROJECT, IS HE GOING TO GIVE
ANSWERS IN TERMS OF WHEN THAT
WENT INTO THE TIME.
>> SOMETHING INTERESTING
HAPPENED OVERNIGHT THAT I WANT
TO GET YOUR TAKE ON, GUYS.
IT WAS AMAZING BACK AND FORTH
THAT TOOK PLACE ON TELEVISION ON
AL JAZEERA INVOLVING ONE OF THE
DOZENS OF FIGURES THAT ARE
INVOLVED IN THIS WHOLE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION AND SPEAKING HERE
OF ERIC PRINCE.
HE IS THE FOUNDER AS YOU ALL
KNOW OF THE CONTROVERSIAL GROUP
THAT IS CALLED BLACK WATER.
HE'S THE BROTHER OF THE
EDUCATION SECRETARY.
SO PRINCE WAS THERE FOR THE
FIRST TIME, IT APPEARS THAT HE
WAS CONFIRMING A "NEW YORK
TIMES" REPORT THAT HE ARRANGED
AN AUGUST 2016 TRUMP TOWER
MEETING BETWEEN DONALD TRUMP JR.
AND MIDDLE EASTERNERS LOOKING TO
HELP TRUMP.
>> I MIGHT HAVE BEEN -- I THINK
I WAS AT TRUMP HEADQUARTERS OR
THE CAMPAIGN HEADQUARTERS --
>> TRUMP TOWER, 2016, YOU AND
ISRAELI DO, DON JUNIOR, STEPHEN
MILLER.
>> WERE THERE TO TALK ABOUT IRAN
POLICY.
>> DON'T YOU THINK THAT WOULD
HAVE BEEN IMPORTANT TO DISCLOSE?
>> I DID.
>> YOU DIDN'T.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF THEY GOT THE
TRANSCRIPT WRONG.
I HAVEN'T HEARD FROM ANYBODY IN
MORE THAN NINE MONTHS.
>> YOU SAY WOW.
>> I KEEP SAYING YOU CAN'T MAKE
IT UP.
I'M IN AWE.
I'M SIMPLY IN AWE AND NOT A GOOD
WAY.
>> HE DOESN'T KNOW IF THEY GOT
THE TRANSCRIPT WRONG.
COULD HE BE IN SOME SORT OF
JEOPARDY RIGHT THERE.
>> THERE'S A WORD FOR WHAT HE IS
RIGHT NOW AND THAT'S TARGET.
I WATCHED THAT INTERVIEW AND
WHEN HE HAS NOTHING LEFT TO FALL
BACK ON, OTHER THAN MAYBE THEY
GOT THE TRANSCRIPT OF MY SWORN
TESTIMONY WRONG, ON THIS BIG
TICKET ISSUE AND THEN HE ADDED,
I HAVEN'T HEARD FROM MUELLER IN
NINE MONTHS OR ANYBODY, WELL,
THAT'S BECAUSE, SPORT, YOU'VE
RIPENED INTO A TARGET BECAUSE
YOU APPARENTLY TESTIFIED FALSELY
ON A MATERIAL MATTER, AN
IMPORTANT MATTER TO THE
CONGRESSIONAL INQUIRY.
I SUSPECT WE'LL SEE HIM INDICTED
IN THE NOT TOO DISTANT FUTURE.
>> I IMAGINE HIS PUBLICISTS WERE
AS UPSET AS R. KELLY'S.
>> ARE WE GOING TO TALK ABOUT
THAT?
>> THERE'S NOT ENOUGH TIME ON
THE 24 HOUR NETWORK.
>>> SO STILL AHEAD, THE
ANTICIPATION IS MOUNTING FOR THE
END OF ROBERT MUELLER'S
INVESTIGATION, BUT DON'T GO
REACHING FOR THE POPCORN YET.
HOW DEMOCRATS ARE PUTTING THE
PRESSURE ON THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT TO RELEASE THE ENTIRE
REPORT?
I AM JOINED LIVE ABOUT
CONGRESSWOMAN SHEILA JACKSON LEE
TO TALK ALL ABOUT.
>>> WE ARE CELEBRATING WOMEN
HISTORY MONTH.
THIS MARCH AND THIS WEEK, WE'RE
PROFILING A DEAL MAKING HER
STORY SOME OF THE
CONGRESSWOMAN'S COLLEAGUES.
DEMOCRATS SHARICE DAVIS AND DEB
HELEN ARE THE FIRST NATIVE
AMERICAN WOMEN RECENTLY ELECTED
TO CONGRESS.
SHE WON KANSAS'S THIRD DISTRICT
SEAT AND HOLLAND WAS ELECTED
NEW MEXICO'S FIRST DISTRICT
SEAT.
CONGRATULATIONS, LADIES.
I'M REALLY INTO THIS CAR,
BUT HOW DO I KNOW IF
I'M GETTING A GOOD DEAL?
I TELL TRUECAR MY ZIP
AND WHICH CAR I WANT
AND TRUECAR SHOWS
THE RANGE OF PRICES
PEOPLE IN MY AREA
ACTUALLY PAID FOR THE SAME CAR
SO I KNOW IF I'M GETTING
A GREAT PRICE.
THIS IS HOW CAR BUYING
WAS ALWAYS MEANT TO BE.
THIS IS TRUECAR.
>>> ANY DAY NOW WE EXPECT THE
SPECIAL COUNSEL TO DELIVER HIS
REPORT TO THE ATTORNEY GENERAL,
BUT WILL IT BE A DROP THE MIC
MOMENT?
THE PUBLIC MAY ONLY GET A SHORT
SUMMARY OF THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATIONS.
MANY DEMOCRATS NOW CONTROL THE
HOUSE AND THEY SAY THEY WILL
DEMAND MUELLER'S FULL REPORT AS
WELL AS THE EVIDENCE BEHIND ALL
OF IT.
JOINING ME NOW IS ONE PARTICULAR
DEMOCRAT WHO IS ASKING FOR THE
FULL REPORT, TEXAS DEMOCRATIC
REPRESENTATIVE SHEILA JACKSON
LEE WHO IS A MEMBER OF THE HOUSE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE.
CONGRESSWOMAN, THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR BEING HERE.
SO YOU JUST GET A SHORTENED
VERSION OF THE REPORT, WHAT'S
YOUR REACTION GOING TO BE?
>> KENDIS, FIRST OF ALL, IT'S A
DELIGHT TO BE HERE WITH YOU AND
LET ME FIRST ACKNOWLEDGE AND
EXPRESS MY CONCERN AND SYMPATHY
FOR THE VICTIMS IN ALABAMA AND
THE HORRIBLE EXPERIENCES THEY'VE
HAD AND THE COMMITMENT BY THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT TO MAKE THEM
WHOLE.
I ABSOLUTELY EXPECT, KENDIS, NOT
TO GET A SUMMARY AND I WILL TURN
ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR'S WORDS
BACK ON HIM WHEN HE WAS PRESSED
BY THE SENATE DURING HIS
CONFIRMATION HEARINGS, HE MADE A
COMMITMENT THAT THE PUBLIC
DESERVED TO HEAR THE RESULTS OF
THE MUELLER REPORT IN FULL.
I WILL ADD THE TERM, IN FULL,
BUT THE RESULTS MEANS THAT YOU
HAVE TO SEE THE REPORT IN FULL
AND IT IS CLEAR THAT THE DOJ
POLICY OF THE LAST TWO YEARS
INDICATED THAT THE PUBLIC CAN
SEE INVESTIGATIVE REPORTS IF IT
IS IN THE PUBLIC INTEREST.
WHAT REPORT COULD BE MORE IN THE
PUBLIC INTEREST THAN THE MUELLER
REPORT?
THE VERY REPORT THAT WAS
DESIGNATED RIGHT AFTER THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
FIRED THE FBI DIRECTOR UNDER A
SPECULATION AND POTENTIAL CHARGE
OF OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE, UNDER
THE ACTUAL WORDS OF THE
PRESIDENT WHO SAID SUBSEQUENT TO
THAT FIRING THAT IT WAS ABOUT
THE RUSSIAN THING, OR SINCE THAT
TIME WE HAVE HEARD FROM ROGER
STONE WHO INDICATED OR COHEN WHO
INDICATED THAT HE WAS IN A
MEETING WITH PRESIDENT TRUMP
WHEN ROGER STONE CALLED ON THE
PHONE AND INDICATED THAT THERE
WOULD BE A DUMP OF WIKILEAKS --
WOULD BE DUMPING THE EMAILS OF
SENATOR CLINTON, SECRETARY
CLINTON, AT THAT TIME, TO RUIN
HER CAMPAIGN.
THERE JUST CANNOT BE ANY EXCUSE
FOR NOT PRESENTING TO THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE THE MUELLER
REPORT.
>> YOU'RE LOOKING FORWARD TO THE
FULL REPORT AS OPPOSED TO CLIFF
NOTES VERSION.
MY COLLEAGUE ARI MELBER SPOKE
WITH THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
CHAIRMAN, YOUR COLLEAGUE, JERRY
NADLER ABOUT THE EXPANSIVE
DOCUMENTS THE COMMITTEE HAS
REQUESTED FROM PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THE PRESIDENT HAS DISMISSED.
COULD THERE BE MORE REQUESTS TO
COME?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
KENDIS, MIGHT I SAY A POINT MORE
AS I SAY IN RESPOND TO THE
QUESTION OF EXPANDING THE LIST
OF INDIVIDUALS, I THINK IT IS
IMPORTANT TO NOTE THAT WE ARE
RESPECTFUL OF THE RULE OF LAW
AND WHERE THERE ARE THIRD
PARTIES THAT ABSOLUTELY ARE NOT
INVOLVED, THOSE NAMES CAN BE
REDACTED.
THIS IS OUT OF THE MUELLER
REPORT, BUT ORDINARILY, EVEN
THIRD PARTIES' NAMES CAN BE
INDICATED AS LONG AS THERE'S
SOME CLARIFICATION THAT THEY'RE
NOT UNDER ANY REVIEW OR
INDICTMENT OR THEY'RE NOT
TARGETS.
>> REALLY QUICKLY, I'M UNDER THE
CRUNCH, OUT OF THE 81 TARGETS ON
THE DOCUMENT REQUEST ITSELF,
IVANKA TRUMP IS NOT INCLUDED.
SHOULD SHE BE AND WILL HER NAME
BE?
>> HERE'S THE POINT I THINK WE
WANT TO BE CAREFUL.
WE WANT TO BE DELIBERATE AND
THERE'S GOING TO BE A SECOND
CRUNCH OF NAMES AND I WOULD
THINK THAT, ONE, THERE'S NO
DOUBT THAT ONE WANTS TO BE
SENSITIVE ABOUT CHILDREN,
GRANDCHILDREN, FAMILY MEMBERS,
BUT AT THE SAME TIME WE WANT THE
TRUTH FOR THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
AS YOU WELL KNOW, ERIC TRUMP IS
ON THE DONALD TRUMP TRUST IS ON,
DONALD TRUMP JR. IS ON.
IT'LL BE A QUESTION OF, AS WE
LOOK AT THE DOCUMENTS, WHO ELSE
NEEDS TO BE ON, NOT FOR THE
NECESSITY OF SAYING WRONG HAS
BEEN DONE, BUT TO GET
INFORMATION REGARDING PUBLIC
CORRUPTION, ABUSE AND
OBSTRUCTION OF THE LAWS.
AND SO THE CLEAR BASIS OF TRYING
TO GET THESE DOCUMENTS IS NOT
HARASSMENT, IT IS CLEARLY WITHIN
THE ARTICLE 1 RESPONSIBILITIES
OF THE CONGRESS AND CERTAINLY IN
THE RESPONSIBILITIES OF THE
HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE, BE
REMINDED THAT FOR THE TWO/THREE
YEARS THE ADMINISTRATION'S BEEN
UNDER SUPERVISION OF THE
REPUBLICAN HOUSE AND SENATE,
THERE'S BEEN NO ACCOUNTABILITY
AND NOW THE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE'S DOING NOTHING MORE
THAN IT'S JOB AND THAT IS TO
HOLD INDIVIDUALS ACCOUNTABLE FOR
ACTS OF CORRUPTION, ABUSE AND
OBSTRUCTION OF JUSTICE.
>> AND INDEED HIGHLIGHTING THE
POINT THAT ELECTIONS HAVE
CONSEQUENCES, INDEED.
REPRESENTATIVE, THANK YOU SO
MUCH FOR BEING HERE ON A
SATURDAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> A SILICON VALLEY BREAK-UP.
WHY ELIZABETH WARREN IS GOING
AFTER BIG TECH COMPANIES LIKE
FACEBOOK, AMAZON AND GOOGLE?
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it from
your allergy pills?
Flonase Sensimist relieves
all your worst symptoms,
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
And all from a gentle mist
you can barely feel.
Flonase Sensimist.
>>> AMAZON?
>> TOO BIG.
>> GOOGLE?
>> FACEBOOK?
>> TOO BIG.
>> MARK ZUCKERBERG?
>> TOO POWERFUL.
>> HUM.
>> AND THAT'S REALLY THE POINT
OF THE TOO BIGS.
IT'S THEY'VE GOT TOO MUCH POWER.
>> VERY INTERESTING THERE.
ELIZABETH WARREN WITH MY
COLLEAGUE JUST LAST NIGHT ON THE
BEAT AND NOW SHE'S ABOUT TO TAKE
ON ALL THOSE BIG TECH GIANTS ON
THEIR HOME TURF.
THE SENATOR'S EXPECTED TO TAKE
THE STAGE IN TEN MINUTES FROM
NOW AT THE SOUTH BY SOUTHWEST
CONFERENCE IN AUSTIN.
IT IS A MECCA FOR CUTTING EDGE
TECH AND NEW MEDIA.
SO WHILE THE ELIZABETH WARREN IS
EXPECTED TO CONTINUE HER PUSH
FOR MORE REGULATION OF TECH
GIANTS, COMPANIES LIKE FACEBOOK
ARE IMPOSING SOME NEW
RESTRICTIONS OF THEIR OWN.
BUSINESS REPORTER BRANDY JOINS
US RIGHT NOW FROM SOUTH BY
SOUTHWEST IN AUSTIN, TEXAS, AND
BRANDI, SENATOR WARREN'S
COMMENTS, HOW ARE THEY BEING
RECEIVED RIGHT NOW AT THIS BIG
TECH FOCUSED FESTIVAL?
>> Reporter: PEOPLE ARE
OBVIOUSLY BUZZING ABOUT IT.
THIS IS THE MOST AGGRESSIVE
THING WE'VE HEARD, THE MOST
AGGRESSIVE PLAN TO BREAK UP THE
BIG TECH COMPANIES.
THIS PLACE IS FULL.
EVERYONE'S TALKING ABOUT IT.
WHO'S NOT TALKING ABOUT IT ARE
THE BIG TECH COMPANIES.
NO ONE'S RELEASED A STATEMENT.
EVERYONE'S WAITING TO HEAR WHAT
THEY HAVE TO SAY ABOUT IT AND
WHAT THE OTHER DEMOCRATIC
CHALLENGERS WILL SAY AS WELL.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE SAY, THIS, OF
COURSE, IS WHERE TWITTER
STARTED.
IT IS WHERE, I BELIEVE, FOUR
SQUARE STARTED, SO WHILE IT MAY
HAVE STARTED 30 YEARS AGO AS BIG
MUSIC FESTIVAL, GIVE ME A SENSE
AND GIVE PEOPLE A SENSE OF THE
IMPORTANCE OF TECHNOLOGY AND SO
MANY OF THESE SOCIAL MEDIA SITES
THERE.
>> Reporter: THIS IS WHERE
EVERYONE COMES TO TALK ABOUT THE
FUTURE OF TECH, SO YOU HAVE, YOU
KNOW, TINY TECH COMPANIES AND
THEN YOU HAVE THE BIG GUYS AND
THEY'RE ALL SORT OF TOGETHER.
THE PROBLEM IS IN WHAT ELIZABETH
WARREN IS SORT OF TRYING TO
COMBAT WITH THIS PLAN IS THE
LITTLE GUYS DON'T NECESSARILY
STAND A CHANCE ANY MORE WITHOUT
BEING SCOOPED UP BY THE BIG
COMPANIES.
IT'S REALLY, REALLY IMPORTANT,
WHATEVER HAPPENS WITH THIS
THAT --
>> DO WE HAVE ANY EXPECTATION ON
WHAT SHE'LL SAY IN JUST A FEW
MINUTES FROM NOW?
>> Reporter: I THINK SHE'LL SAY
THE SAME THING SHE SAID IN LONG
ISLAND CITY.
SHE'S LAYING OUT HER PLAN SEEING
IF PEOPLE IN LONG ISLAND CITY
WERE RECEPTIVE TO IT.
THEY WERE THE HOME THAT AMAZON
DECIDED NOT TO GO TO, BUT HERE
WHERE IT'S EVERY BIG TECH
COMPANY AGAIN IS HERE AND THE
REPRESENTATIVES ARE HERE, I'M
CURIOUS TO SEE HOW IT'S GOING TO
BE RECEIVED.
>> ALL RIGHT.
BRANDY THERE IN AUSTIN.
THERE'S QUITE A BIT OF
ENTHUSIASM AS PEOPLE ARE QUITE
LOUD THERE.
BRANDY, THANK YOU.
>>> MANY OF MY NBC NEWS
COLLEAGUES WILL BE THERE THIS
WEEKEND.
THEY'LL BE PART OF PANELS ABOUT
INVESTIGATIVE REPORTING, THE
SPREAD OF FAKE NEWS ONLINE AS
WELL AS SELF-DRIVING CARS.
FOR MORE INFORMATION AND WHERE
TO SEE THEM, FOLLOW NBC NEWS ON
TWITTER.
>>> THE WHITE HOUSE SAID, NO WAY
TO DEMOCRATS, BUT NOW THE HOUSE
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE REPORTEDLY
HAS DOCUMENTS REVEALING JUST HOW
JARED AND IVANKA GOT THEIR
SECURITY CLEARANCES.
DID THE PRESIDENT ABUSE HIS
POWER TO GET THEM TOP SECURITY
ACCESS?
If you have postmenopausal
osteoporosis
and a high risk for fracture
now might not be the best time
to ask yourself
are my bones strong?
Life is full of make-or-break
moments.
That's why it's so important
to help reduce your risk of
fracture with Prolia®.
Only Prolia® is proven to help
strengthen
and protect bones from fracture
with 1 shot every 6 months.
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take
XGEVA®.
Serious allergic reactions,
like low blood pressure; trouble
breathing;
throat tightness; face, lip, or
tongue swelling;
rash; itching; or hives have
happened.
Tell your doctor about dental
problems
as severe jaw bone problems may
happen
or new or unusual pain in your
hip groin, or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone fractures
have occurred.
Speak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects,
like low blood calcium, serious
infections,
which could need
hospitalization, skin problems,
and severe bone, joint, or
muscle pain.
Are you ready?
Ask your doctor how Prolia® can
help strengthen your bones.
♪
Audible members know
listening has the power
to change us make us better
parents,
better leaders, better people.
And there's no better place
to listen than Audible.
With Audible you get a credit
good for any audiobook and
exclusive fitness
and wellness programs.
And now, you'll also get two
Audible originals:
titles exclusively
produced for Audible.
Automatically roll
your credits over
to the next month if
you don't use them,
and if you don't like a book
just swap it for free.
Enjoy 100% ad free
listening in the car,
on your phone or
any connected device.
And when you switch a device
pick up right where
you left off.
With our commitment
free guarantee,
there's never been
a better time
to start listening
to Audible.
The most inspiring minds, the
most compelling stories,
the best place to listen.
To start your free
30-day trial,
text Listen14 to
500500 today.
♪