YOU WANT TO SIGN THE BIBLE, THAT
IS ONE DEBATE.
I SUGGEST YOU OPEN IT UP AND
BEGIN READING IT OR NEXT TIME
YOU'RE ASKED, DON'T PROFESS TO
BE ONE THAT PRACTICES IT AND AT
LEAST ONE OR TWO VERSES THAT
MEAN SOMETHING TO YOU BECAUSE
MAYBE ALL OF IT AS YOU SAID WAS
WHAT YOUR FAVORITE IS IS TOO
MUCH TO CONSUME AND PRACTICE AT
THE SAME TIME.
THAT DOES IT FOR ME.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
SEE YOU BACK HERE NEXT SATURDAY
AT 5:00 P.M. EASTERN.
UNTIL THEN, KEEP THE
CONVERSATION GOING.
LIKE US @FACEBOOK.COM/POLITICS
NATION.
AND FOLLOW US ON
TWITTER @POLITICS NATION.
>>> UP NEXT, "MEET THE PRESS"
WITH CHUCK TODD.
>>> THIS SUNDAY, DIVIDED
DEMOCRATS.
BERNIE VERSUS BIDEN.
PROGRESSIVES VERSUS TRADITIONAL
DEMOCRATS.
HIGHLIGHTED BY THIS COMMENT FROM
FRESHMAN CONGRESSWOMAN ILHAN
OMAR.
>> I WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE
POLITICAL INFLUENCE IN THIS
COUNTRY THAT SAYS IT IS OKAY FOR
PEOPLE TO PUSH FOR ALLEGIANCE TO
A FOREIGN COUNTRY.
>> SOME FELLOW DEMOCRATS HERE
BIGOTRY.
>> THE USE OF ANTI-SEMITIC
LANGUAGE AND IMAGES CAN NEVER BE
TOLERATED.
>> OTHERS RUSHED TO HER DEFENSE.
>> I HEAR HER TRYING TO LIFT UP
MY GRANDMOTHER IN THE WEST BANK.
>> REAL FISSURES IN THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY WITH
IMPLICATION FOR 2020.
MY GUESTS THIS MORNING, SHERROD
BROWN OF OHIO AND LIZ CHENEY,
CHAIR OF THE HOUSE REPUBLICAN
CONFERENCE.
>>> PLUS, WAITING FOR BIDEN.
ER HAVE SHERROD BROWN NOT
RUNNING.
BLOOMBERG, NOT RUNNING.
BOTH LIKELY OUT BECAUSE THEY ARE
EXPECTING JOE BIDEN TO GET IN.
>> I HAVEN'T MADE THE FINAL
DECISION.
DON'T BE SURPRISED.
>> WHAT IS BIDEN WAITING FOR?
>>> AND PARDON ME?
DID MICHAEL COHEN ASK PRESIDENT
TRUMP FOR A PARDON?
>> I HAVE NEVER ASKED FOR A
PARDON.
NOR WOULD I ACCEPT A PARDON.
>> THAT'S A STONE-COLD LIE.
>> I'LL TALK ABOUT THAT, THE
MANAFORT SENTENCING AND THE
LATEST ON THE RUSSIAN
INVESTIGATION, WITH THE CHAIR OF
THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE, ADAM SCHIFF.
JOINING US IS KASIE HUNT.
ROBERT COSTA, MODERATOR OF
"WASHINGTON WEEK."
MARIA TERESA KUMAR.
PRESIDENT OF VIDEO -- VOTO
LATINO.
AND THE FORMER REPUBLICAN
GOVERNOR OF NORTH CAROLINA,
PRESIDENT MccCRORY.
WELCOME TO SUNDAY, AND "MEET THE
PRESS."
>> THIS IS "MEET THE PRESS,"
WITH CHUCK TODD.
>> GOOD SUNDAY MORNING.
NEVER MIND THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S CAMPAIGN CHAIRMAN IS
GOING TO PRISON AND THAT MR.
TRUMP AND MICHAEL COHEN ARGUED
THIS WEEK OVER WHICH ONE OF THEM
IS LYING ABOUT A POSSIBLE
PARDON.
OUR COLLEAGUE, DANA MILBANK AT
"THE WASHINGTON POST" POINTED
OUT, THAT WITH PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
STRUGGLES WITH NORTH KOREA, ON
THE TRADE DEFICIT, THE BORDER
WALL, THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
THAT CAN SAVE HIM, THE
DEMOCRATS.
AS HE SAID, RIGHT ON CUE, HERE
THEY COME.
DEMOCRATS HAVE SPENT MUCH OF THE
LAST MONTH WRESTLING THEMSELVES
TO THE GROUND.
THEY WERE EMBARRASSED OVER RALPH
NORTHAM HAD ONCE DRESSED IN
BLACKFACE.
AND STARTLED BY SEXUAL
HARASSMENT COMMENTS BY NORTHAM'S
LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR, JUSTIN
FAIRFAX.
AND CHRONICALLY UNSURE TO HANDLE
A COMMENT BY OMAR.
AND EMERGING GROUP OF DEMOCRATS
IS CONTINUING INTO CONFLICT WITH
THE LIBERALS.
THEY'RE UNITED AND DIVIDED.
THEY'RE UNITED ABOUT THE URGENCY
OF DEFEATING PRESIDENT TRUMP
NEXT YEAR.
AT THE SAME TIME, THEY ARE
DIVIDED, WITH EACH SIDE SEEING
THE OTHER AS THE REASON MR.
TRUMP MAY WIND UP WINNING AFTER
ALL.
>> YOU APOLOGIZED FOR YOUR LAST
REMARKS.
HOW ARE THEY DIFFERENT?
>> Reporter: CONGRESSWOMAN OMAR
DREW CRITICISM AFTER TWEETING
THAT U.S. POLITICIANS SUPPORT
ISRAEL BECAUSE IT'S ALL ABOUT
THE BENJAMINS, BABY.
SHE APOLOGIZED BUT THEN MADE
THIS COMMENT LAST WEEK.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
POLITICAL INFLUENCE IN THIS
COUNTRY THAT SAYS IT IS OKAY FOR
PEOPLE TO PUSH FOR ALLEGIANCE TO
A FOREIGN COUNTRY.
>> JEWS HAVE DUAL LOYALTY AND
CANNOT BE PATRIOTIC MEMBERS OF
THE COUNTRY IN WHICH THEY LIVE?
WORDS MATTER.
>> Reporter: SOME PROGRESSIVES
DEFENDED OMAR, POINTING TO SLURS
AGAINST HER.
LIKE THIS FLYER IN WEST
VIRGINIA.
>> WE THINK THAT HATE AND RACISM
IN OUR COUNTRY IS GROWING, IF
YOU'RE JEWISH, LGBTQ,
LATINO, IMMIGRANTS, MUSLIM.
>> Reporter: HOUSE DEMOCRATS
UNITED AROUND A BROAD RESOLUTION
CONDEMNING HATE.
AFTER AN OFFICIAL DRAFT THAT
REBUKED ANTI-SEMITISM.
THE ISSUE IS DIVIDING 2020
DEMOCRATS.
>> I THINK IT WAS RIGHT IN THIS
CASE TO DEMONSTRATE THAT THE
HOUSE OF REPUBLICANS WASN'T ABLE
TO TOLERATE HATEFUL STATEMENTS.
>> Reporter: BUT TOP
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES, WHILE
CONDEMNING ANTI-SEMITISM, SAYS
THAT OMAR WAS UNFAIRLY TARGETED.
THE DEBATE IS EXPOSING
IDEOLOGICAL, GENERATIONAL AND
RACIAL DIVIDES IN THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY.
AS THE PROGRESSIVE LEFT IS
SHOWING ITS STRENGTH.
>> IT IS TIME TO BREAK UP THE
TECH GIANTS.
>> Reporter: SOME DEMOCRATS ARE
RELUCTANT TO EMBRACE CAPITALISM.
>> YOU KNOW, AGAIN, THE LABELS
I'M NOT SURE ANY OF THEM FIT.
>> Reporter: CHAMPIONING THE
GREEN NEW DEAL.
>> DOES THE GREEN NEW DEAL GO
TOO FAR?
>> NO.
YOU CANNOT GO TOO FAR ON THE
ISSUE OF CLIMATE CHANGE.
>> Reporter: AND CALLING FOR
MEDICARE FOR ALL.
>> DO YOU THINK ELIMINATING
PRIVATE INSURANCE WOULD BE A
SOCIALIST IDEA?
>> NO.
I STRONGLY BELIEVE WE NEED TO
HAVE MEDICARE FOR ALL.
>> Reporter: CAN A CENTRIST
CANDIDATE BREAK THROUGH IN A
PARTY THAT IS SHIFTING TO THE
LEFT?
>> WHY SHOULD WE ELECT A
CANDIDATE THAT SAYS, IT'S NOT
POSSIBLE TO DO EVERYTHING THAT
PROGRESSIVES WANT?
>> BECAUSE I'M BEING HONEST.
>> Reporter: THIS WEEK, MICHAEL
BLOOMBERG AND OHIO SENATOR,
SHERROD BROWN, SAID NO THANKS TO
A PRESIDENTIAL RUN, WITH FORMER
VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN POISED
TO JUMP INTO THE RACE.
>> I HAVE NOT MADE THE FINAL
DECISION.
BUT DON'T BE SURPRISED.
>> Reporter: BEFORE HIS RUN IS
OFFICIAL, BIDEN IS EXPLAINING A
DECADES-LONG RECORD, INCLUDING
HIS ROLE IN PASSING THE NOW
CONTROVERSIAL 1994 CRIME BILL.
HIS VOTE FOR THE IRAQ WAR,
SKEPTICISM OF ANITA HILL AND
PAST COMMENTS ON BUSSING TO
DESEGREGATE SCHOOLS.
>> I HAVE BEEN IN THIS FIGHT FOR
A LONG TIME.
I HAVEN'T ALWAYS BEEN RIGHT.
I KNOW WE HAVEN'T ALWAYS GOTTEN
THINGS RIGHT.
BUT I'VE ALWAYS TRIED.
>> AND JOINING ME NOW FROM
CLEVELAND, IS DEMOCRATIC
GOVERNOR SHERROD BROWN, WHO
ANNOUNCED TO THE SURPRISE OF
MANY, THAT HE DECIDED NOT TO RUN
FOR PRESIDENT IN 2020.
WELCOME BACK TO "MEET THE
PRESS."
>> GOOD TO BE BACK.
THANKS.
>> COLOR US VERY SURPRISED.
IN FACT, THE LAST TIME I WERE
ON, MY EXECUTIVE PRODUCER NOTED
HE WAS SPEAKING ABOUT HIS
PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN IN THE
PRESENT TENSE.
IT SEEMED SO IMMINENT TO US.
YOU DID SURPRISE A LOT OF
PEOPLE.
YOU HAD BEGUN TO HIRE SOME
WHAT CHANGED YOUR MIND?
>> AS YOU KNOW, CHUCK, THIS
STARTED OFF BECAUSE I DON'T
THINK DEMOCRATS WERE TALKING TO
WORKING-CLASS AMERICANS OF ALL
RACES ENOUGH.
IF YOU LOVE YOUR COUNTRY, YOU
WILL FIGHT FOR THE PEOPLE WHO
MAKE IT WORK, WE BEGAN OUR
DIGNITY OF WORK TOUR.
IN FOUR STATES.
WE HIRED PEOPLE TO HELP US WITH
THE TOUR AND TO BE READY.
OUR GOAL WAS TO INFORM THE
NARRATIVE IN THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY, SO THAT DEMOCRATS TALKED
MORE TO WORKERS AND A NUMBER OF
CANDIDATES HAVE ALREADY DONE
THAT.
HAVE BEEN TALKING ABOUT THE
DIGNITY OF WORK.
I PREDICT THAT THE DEMOCRATIC
NOMINEE IS THE ONE THAT TALKS TO
WORKERS THE BEST.
AND I'M NOT JUST TALKING ABOUT
WORKERS IN THE INDUSTRIAL
MIDWEST.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE PHYSICAL
THERAPISTS IN NEVADA AND THE
CONSTRUCTION WORKER IN NEW
HAMPSHIRE AND THE HOSPITAL
WORKER IN BALTIMORE.
I WOULD PREDICT, IF I COULD DO
THIS, THAT COME JANUARY 20th,
2021, THAT IN THE INAUGURAL,
WHEN THE DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENT-ELECT RAISES HER OR
HIS RIGHT HAND, THEY WILL LAUNCH
INTO A SPEECH, THEIR INAUGURAL
SPEECH WILL TALK ABOUT THE
DIGNITY OF WORK.
IT'S NOT JUST A SLOGAN, IT'S WHO
I AM AND WHAT WE FIGHT FOR.
BUT MOST IMPORTANTLY, IT'S HOW
WE GOVERN.
>> TO REINFORCE WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING, WE PUT TOGETHER A
COLLECTION OF FOLKS THAT STOLE
YOUR LINE.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> WE HAVE TO REWARD AND
RECOGNIZE THE DIGNITY OF WORK.
>> THERE IS DIGNITY IN ALL WORK
AND CAREER PROFESSIONALS.
>> WE HAVE TO GIVE IT THE
DIGNITY OF THE WORK BEING
PERFORMED.
>> SENATOR, YOUR MESSAGE, YOU'RE
DOING SOMETHING THAT MANY
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES WISH
COULD HAVE HAPPENED TO THEM.
YOUR INITIAL MESSAGE BEGINS TO
RESONATE TO THE POINT THAT YOU
HAVE COMPETITORS STEALING YOUR
LINES.
SO LET ME ASK YOU THIS.
HOW DO YOU NOT RUN?
IT WAS RESONATING AND YOU STILL
SAID NO.
>> IT WAS RESONATING AND I WOULD
SAY MISSION ACCOMPLISHED BUT I'M
NOT DONE YET.
I CAN DO THAT BETTER FROM THE
SENATE.
WE SPENT THREE MONTHS TALKING
ABOUT THE DIGNITY OF WORK.
I'LL CONTINUE TO DO THAT.
I WENT TO THE FLOOR AFTER I
ANNOUNCED I WASN'T GOING TO RUN
AND TALKED ABOUT CIVIL RIGHTS
AND VOTING RIGHTS AND WORKER
RIGHTS AND A SUPREME COURT THAT
PUTS ITS THUMB ON THE SCALES OF
JUSTICE, IN FAVORING
CORPORATIONS OVER WORKERS AND
HEALTH INSURANCE COMPANY OVER
SICK PEOPLE AND WALL STREET OVER
CONSUMERS.
I WILL CONTINUE THAT ECONOMIC
POPULOUS FIGHT, ALWAYS THROUGH
THE EYES OF WORKERS.
IT'S WHAT WE ARE AS A PARTY.
I THINK I CAN DRIVE THAT BETTER
FROM THE SENATE THAN I CAN AS
ONE OUT OF 15, 20 PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES.
>> WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU
TALKED TO JOE BIDEN?
>> OCTOBER.
>> SO, YOU HAVEN'T TALKED TO HIM
RECENTLY?
THIS WASN'T HIM CALLING AROUND,
LETTING PEOPLE KNOW HE'S
RUNNING?
>> IT WAS NONE OF THAT.
I KNOW THAT THAT'S BEEN
REPORTED.
BUT THE PEOPLE THAT REPORTED
THAT NEVER CALLED ME, NEVER
CALLED CONNIE, NEVER CALLED
SARAH BENZENE, MY CHIEF OF
STAFF.
NEVER CALLED MY COMMUNICATIONS
DIRECTOR.
I LIKE JOE BIDEN.
I JUST HAVEN'T TALKED TO HIM.
PEOPLE ASK ME IN ALMOST EVERY
ONE OF THE STATES, IS JOE BIDEN
GETTING IN HAVING AN IMPACT ON
YOUR DECISION?
AND MY ANSWER WAS ALWAYS ZERO.
>> WHEN PEOPLE WERE ASSESSING
YOUR CANDIDACY, YOU WERE SEEN AS
ONE OF THE FOLKS THAT COULD
BRIDGE THIS DIVIDE.
YOU'RE A GUY THAT FIGURED OUT
HOW TO WIN IN THE RED STATE.
BUT ALSO HAD KEPT TO SOME
PROGRESSIVE PRINCIPLES.
IN FACT, HERE'S WHAT YOU TOLD
THE NATION IN AN INTERVIEW.
YOU SAID, IF I RUN, I WILL BE
THE ONLY DEMOCRAT ON THE STAGE
WHO WILL HAVE VOTED AGAINST THE
IRAQ WAR, WHO WILL HAVE VOTED
AGAINST THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE
ACT, WHICH MEANS FOR MARRIAGE
EQUALITY, AND WHO WILL BE
PRO-CHOICE 100% OVER THE YEARS.
WHAT WAS INTERESTING, IT WAS
YOUR WAY OF SAYING, I'M AN
EXPERIENCED DEMOCRAT BUT ON THE
PROGRESSIVE SIDE OF THE LANE IN
WAYS THAT OTHER DEMOCRATS,
PERHAPS YOU'RE REFERRING TO JOE
BIDEN, WERE NOT.
>> I WAS REFERRING TO NOBODY IN
PARTICULAR.
I WAS JUST SAYING THAT I'VE BEEN
A STRONG PROGRESSIVE FOR YEARS.
I WILL CARRY THAT BACK TO THE
SENATE.
I WILL BE PART OF THIS
PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN, IN TERMS
OF CALLING OUT THIS PRESIDENT
FOR HIS PHONY POPULISM.
POPULISM IS NEVER RACIST OR
ANTI-SEMITIC.
POPULISM DOESN'T DIVIDE PEOPLE.
POPULISM DON'T GIVE TAX CUTS TO
THE RICHEST PEOPLE OF THE
COUNTRY AND TRY TO CUT MEDICARE
AND HEAD START.
I WILL POINT OUT HOW THIS
PRESIDENT HAS BETRAYED THE AUTO
WORKERS AND HOSPITAL WORKERS.
I WILL CONTINUE TO MAKE THAT
CASE FROM THE FLOOR OF THE
SENATE, FROM TRAVELS AROUND THE
COUNTRY, BY NOT YET SUPPORTING
ANY PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE BUT
MOVING THE DEBATE FORWARD ABOUT
DIGNITY OF WORK.
>> LET ME ASK YOU THIS -- IS
THERE A DANGER OF GOING TOO FAR
TO THE LEFT THAT IT MIGHT SCARE
SOME VOTERS, SAY, IN OHIO?
>> I HEAR THE STORIES THAT ARE,
THAT'S THE STORY OF THE DAY,
ABOUT DEMOCRATS MOVING TO THE
LEFT.
I THINK THE MORE IMPORTANT STORY
UP
IS HOW REPUBLICANS CONTINUE TO
MOVE TO THE RIGHT, HOW PRESIDENT
TRUMP EXTOLS -- BETRAYS WORKERS
AND UTTERS RACIST, ANTI-SEMITIC
RHETORIC.
NOBODY IN THEIR PARTY CALLS THEM
OUT.
THEY DON'T HAVE DIVISIONS.
THEY'VE FOLLOWED HIS RACIST
ACTIONS AND BETRAYAL OF WORKERS.
THEY FOLLOW IT LIKE LEMMINGS OFF
THE CLIFF.
THAT'S THE STORY, NOT SOME
DEGREES OF DIFFERENCES BETWEEN
AND AMONG DEMOCRATS.
THAT'S THE REAL STORY.
>> LET ME ASK YOU THIS.
WHAT IS FAIR GAME?
YOU IN THAT INTERVIEW SAID, IN
1996, WHEN IT WASN'T A POPULAR
THING TO DO, YOU VOTED AGAINST
THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE ACT, FOR
INSTANCE.
JOE BIDEN HAS COMMENTS ABOUT
BUSSING AND DESEGREGATION OF
SCHOOLS THAT ARE POPPING UP,
QUOTES FROM HIM IN THE '70s.
YOU CAN MAKE THE ARGUMENT THAT
WAS THE MAINSTREAM DEMOCRATIC
PARTY POSITION, PERHAPS, IN THE
'70s.
SHOULD THOSE COMMENTS MATTER TO
VOTERS IN IOWA, TO DEMOCRATS IN
IOWA IN THE 21st CENTURY?
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT
SHERROD BROWN THINKS ABOUT THE
MATTERS TO VOTERS IN IOWA?
>> DOES IT MATTER TO YOU?
>> RECORDS MATTER TO ME.
THE CANDIDATE THAT IS TALKING --
I GO BACK TO, WHAT ARE THEY
GOING TO DO ABOUT TALKING TO
WORKERS AND THE DIGNITY OF WORK.
I WANT TO SEE DIGNITY OF WORK,
NOT JUST PART OF THIS CAMPAIGN,
NOT JUST A SLOGAN, NOT JUST WHAT
THE CANDIDATES TALK ABOUT, I
WANT TO MAKE SURE THEY GOVERN
BASED ON THE DIGNITY OF WORK.
REGARDLESS OF THE WORK YOU DO,
IT'S ABOUT WAGES OR BENEFITS.
WORKPLACE SAFETY, ABOUT CHILD
CARE, IN THE NEVADA -- IN THE
CULINARY WORKERS UNION HALL IN
LAS VEGAS, CONNIE AND I WERE
THERE THREE OR FOUR WEEKS AGO,
THEIR SLOGAN IS, ONE JOB SHOULD
BE ENOUGH.
I WANT TO HEAR WORKERS START
TALKING ABOUT THAT, THAT ONE
LIVING WAGE JOB SHOULD BE
ENOUGH.
WITH HEALTH CARE, WITH
RETIREMENT, WITH CHILD CARE,
WITH SAFETY IN THE WORKPLACE.
THAT'S EVERYTHING, TO ME IN THIS
RACE.
THAT'S A WINNING MESSAGE AND
IT'S THE WAY WE SHOULD GOVERN,
STARTING IN 2021.
>> I'M GOING TO CLOSE WITH THE
SAME QUESTION I ASKED YOU AT THE
BEGINNING.
I DIDN'T HEAR AN ANSWER WHY YOU
DIDN'T RUN.
IS IT SIMPLY, YOU DIDN'T WANT TO
DO IT?
>> I THINK WE WERE SUCCESSFUL IN
MOVING FORWARD AS WE HAVE.
I -- I WAS TALKING TO SOME
PEOPLE ABOUT THIS.
YOU CAN RUN IN THREE DIFFERENT
WAYS.
YOU CAN RUN AS EEIOR, I DIDN'T
WANT TO DO DO THAT OR BE THE
ANGRY CANDIDATE, I DIDN'T WANT
TO DO THAT.
OR YOU CAN RUN AS AN OPTIMIST,
JOYFUL CANDIDATE, THE WAY I DO
MY JOB IN THE SENATE.
I THINK I CAN DO THAT BETTER IN
THE SENATE, IN CONTINUING TO
PERFORM THIS PRESIDENTIAL
CHOICE.
>> YOU'RE SAYING YOU CAN'T RUN
FOR PRESIDENT JOYFULLY.
THAT'S WHAT I JUST HEARD.
SORRY.
>> I THINK I CAN DO IT BETTER IN
THE SENATE.
>> FAIR ENOUGH.
LEAVE IT AT THAT, CHUCK.
>> SENATOR SHERROD BROWN.
>> IT'S ALWAYS JOYFUL BEING ON
YOUR SHOW.
>> THAT, I APPRECIATE.
IT'S SUNDAY MORNING, CUP OF
COFFEE AND YOU SPRUNG FORWARD.
THAT I APPRECIATE.
>> EVEN WHEN THE TIME CHANGES
AND YOU MAKE ME GET UP AN HOUR
EARLIER.
>> SENATOR --
>> AND YOU BROADCAST IT LATER
AND PEOPLE DON'T KNOW HOW EARLY
WE GOT UP.
>> YOU AN YOUR OHIO COLLEAGUE,
JOHN KASICH, YOU GUYS KNOW HOW
TO TALK TO YOUR OHIO VOTERS.
THANK YOU, SIR.
MUCH APPRECIATED.
JOINING ME NOW IS THE CHAIR
OF THE HOUSE REPUBLICAN
CONFERENCE, CONGRESSWOMAN LIZ
CHENEY.
I WANT TO START WITH WHAT
HAPPENED IN THE HOUSE THIS WEEK.
IT WAS A BIT OF A SURPRISE.
YOU VOTED AGAINST THIS BROAD
RESOLUTION.
AND WHILE YOUR CRITICISM OF THE
RESOLUTION, I TOTALLY
UNDERSTAND.
BUT YOU WERE IN THE MINORITY OF
YOUR PARTY.
DID YOUR FELLOW HOUSE
REPUBLICANS MAKE A MISTAKE BY
VOTING WITH THE DEMOCRATS ON
THIS RESOLUTION?
>> NO.
I THINK THERE WERE TWO WAYS WE
COULD HAVE GONE.
SOME OF THE PEOPLE IN OUR
CONFERENCE LOOKED AT IT AND
SAID, THERE'S NOTHING
OBJECTIONABLE IN THE RESOLUTION.
MY STATEMENT MADE CLEAR THAT
THAT WAS MY VIEW AS WELL.
I DECIDED TO VOTE AGAINST IT
BECAUSE I THINK IT WAS AN EFFORT
PROTECT ILHAN OMAR, TO COVER UP
HER BIGOTRY AND ANTI-SEMITISM BY
REFUSING TO NAME HER.
THE DEMOCRATS HAVE YET TO TAKE
ANY ACTION TO REMOVE HER FROM
HER COMMITTEE.
AND THEY HAVE A REAL PROBLEM.
THE EXTENT TO WHICH THEY ARE
ABIDING BY ANTI-SEMITISM,
ENABLING ANTI-SEMITISM IN THEIR
PARTY IS SOMETHING THEY STRUGGLE
WITH.
BUT SOMETIMES IT'S VERY
DANGEROUS FOR THE COMPANY.
I'M HOPEFUL THEY WILL BE ABLE TO
STAND UP AND DO THE RIGHT THING
ON THIS.
>> THERE WAS SOME CRITICISM,
SOME PEOPLE WERE PEEVED AT
CHENEY, MEANING YOU.
THINKING THAT AMONG MOST TOP
REPUBLICANS ARE THIS.
WHEN YOU'RE A LEADERSHIP TEAM,
YOU STICK TOGETHER.
THE CRITICISM BEING, SINCE
YOU'RE A MEMBER OF LEADERSHIP,
YOU SHOULD HAVE SPOKEN WITH ONE
VOICE.
>> I THINK, YOU KNOW HOW THE
HILL WORKS.
THOSE ANONYMOUS SOURCES THAT ARE
OUT THERE SNIPING.
THE IMPORTANT THING FOR US TO BE
FOCUSED ON AND REMEMBER, THE
DEMOCRATS HAVE BEEN IN CHARGE
FOR ABOUT 2 1/2 MONTHS IN THE
HOUSE.
IN THAT TIME, THEY'VE BEEN THE
PARTY OF ANTI-SEMITISM, THE
PARTY OF INFANTICIDE, THE PARTY
OF SOCIALISM.
THEY PASSED LEGISLATION THAT
VIOLATED THE FIRST AND THE
SECOND AMENDMENT.
IT'S REALLY TIME FOR THE
DEMOCRATS, THE LEADERSHIP IN
THAT PARTY, TO STOP IT, TO STAND
UP AND TO ACT WORTHY, FRANKLY,
OF THE TRUST THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
HAVE PLACED IN THEM.
IT'S CRUCIAL FOR THE NATION.
>> I WANT TO UNPACK A COUPLE
THINGS.
FIRST, ON THE ISSUE OF -- YOU
THINK CONGRESSMAN OMAR SHOULD
LOSE HER COMMITTEE ASSIGNMENTS.
YOU FOUGHT FOR STEVE KING TO BE
STRIPPED OF HIS COMMITTEE
ASSIGNMENTS.
WHY SHOULD CONGRESSIONAL LEADERS
DO THIS?
IF THE VOTERS SEND THESE FOLKS
-- THE VOTERS IN WESTERN IOWA
KNOW STEVE KING.
FOR BETTER OR WORSE.
AND THE VOTERS IN MINNESOTA KNEW
HER COMMENTS WERE VERY MUCH
WELL-PUBLICIZED.
IF THEY SEND THEM THERE, SHOULD
CONGRESSIONAL LEADERS REALLY BE
TELLING -- BE STRIPPING, NOT
ALLOWING THEM ON COMMITTEES?
>> THE POINT IS, VOTERS SEND
THEM THERE.
NOBODY IS SAYING WE'RE GOING TO
EXPEL THEM.
WE RESPECT THE DECISIONS THAT
THE VOTERS HAVE MADE.
BUT THERE ARE CERTAIN THINGS
THAT SHOULDN'T BE PART OF THE
PUBLIC DISCOURSE.
WHITE SUPREMACY IS ONE OF THOSE.
AND ANTI-SEMITISM, THE HISTORY
OF WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU DON'T
STAND UP TO THE EVIL, THE
HISTORY OF HOW QUICKLY WORDS
TURN INTO SOMETHING MORE
HORRIBLE WHEN IT COMES TO
ANTI-SEMITISM.
AS A NATION, WE MUST, AT ALL
TIMES, STAND UP TO IT.
AND THE KIND OF ANTI-SEMITISM
THAT YOU'RE SEEING FROM ILHAN
OMAR AND BEING SUPPORTED BY HER
COLLEAGUES IS A KIND OF
ANTI-SEMITISM THAT CAN CREEP IN
AND BEING NORMALIZED IN OUR
DISCOURSE AND WE HAVE AN
OBLIGATION NOT TO LET THAT
HAPPEN.
>> THERE IS AN ANTI-SEMITISM
THAT HAS CREPT IN.
LOOK AT GEORGE SOROS.
THE REPUBLICAN ATTACKS OVER
GEORGE SOROS.
AND KEVIN McCARTHY HAD TO PULL
ONE TWEET THAT HE WAS TRYING TO
BUY THIS OR BUY THAT.
THAT'S GOTTEN MAINSTREAMED TO
THE POINT THAT GEORGE SOROS SAID
THAT SOME GUY WAS TRYING TO PIPE
BOMB HIM.
THIS WHAT ABOUTISM, WHERE
EVERYBODY TRIES TO POINT TO THE
OTHER SIDE --
>> CHUCK, CHUCK --
>> AND IT'S GETTING --
>> THE WHAT ABOUTISM SHOULD NOT
GO ON.
AND EVERYONE, INCLUDING LEADER
McCARTHY HAS STOOD UP FIRMLY TO
CONDEMN ANTI-SEMITISM.
THE THING THAT PEOPLE NEED TO BE
FOCUSED ON IS THE DEMOCRATS IN
THE HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES AND
SOME OF THE DEMOCRATS
THEMSELVES, ARE COMPLETELY
FRUSTRATED WITH THE FACT THAT
THE LEADERSHIP IS -- THEY ARE
PROTECTING HER.
THIS ISN'T JUST BEING SILENT.
THEY ARE PROTECTING HER, BY
FAILING TO PUT A RESOLUTION ON
THE FLOOR THAT NAMES HER AND
THAT STRIPS HER OF HER COMMITTEE
ASSIGNMENT.
INSTEAD, THEY PUT A RESOLUTION
ON THE FLOOR THAT SHE SAID THIS
IS A TREMENDOUS VICTORY FOR ME.
NOW, IF WE ARE NOT GOING TO BE
IN A POSITION WHERE YOU SAY THE
KIND OF LANGUAGE THAT SHE HAS
SAID, AGAIN AND AGAIN AND AGAIN,
IS ABSOLUTELY UNACCEPTABLE AND
HAS NO PLACE IN OUR DISCOURSE,
THEN THOSE PEOPLE WHO WON'T
CONDEMN IT ARE ENABLING IT.
>> THERE WAS CONCERN BY SINGLING
HER OUT, YOU ONLY MAKE A TARGET
AND THEY POINTED TO THE WEST
VIRGINIA REPUBLICAN PARTY FLYER.
>> CHUCK, I'M SORRY --
>> BUT MY POINT IS WE'RE
GETTING --
>> YOU CAN DESCRIBE IT THAT WAY,
CHUCK.
>> WE'RE GETTING IN A DANGEROUS
WAY IF WE DO THIS.
>> BUT YOU ARE WRONG.
YOU HAVE A SITUATION IN THIS
COUNTRY AND AROUND THE WORLD
WHERE WE'VE SEEN THE GLOBAL RISE
OF ANTI-SEMITIC ATTACKS, YOU
HAVE THE KIND OF ATTACKS WE HAD
ON THE SYNAGOGUE HERE IN THE
UNITED STATES RECENTLY.
THAT'S A MOTIVE --
>> THAT WAS MOTIVATED BY FRINGE
IDEOLOGY.
>> ANTI-SEMITIC, NO MATTER WHERE
IT COMES FROM, IS WRONG.
WHEN YOU'RE IN A SITUATION WHERE
YOU ARE AN ELECTED OFFICIAL, WE
HAVE THE HISTORY THAT WE HAVE,
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU DON'T
STAND UP AND SAY THIS IS EVIL,
AND CALL IT WHAT IT IS.
WE HAVE AN OBLIGATION TO DO
THAT.
AND I THINK IT IS SHAMEFUL THAT
NANCY PELOSI AND LEADER HOYER
AND DEMOCRATIC LEADERS WILL NOT
PUT HER NAME IN THE RESOLUTION
ON THE FLOOR AND CONDEMN HER
REMARKS AND REMOVE HER FROM THE
HOUSE FOREIGN --
>> YOU FEEL THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
HAS DONE ENOUGH TO TAMP DOWN THE
RIGHT-WING FRINGE ANTI-SEMITISM
THAT'S COMING UP?
>> I DON'T BELIEVE IT'S RIGHT OR
LEFT.
THIS IS AN ISSUE WHERE WE SHOULD
ALL COME TOGETHER, THE
PRESIDENT, THE VICE PRESIDENT,
THE SENATE, THE HOUSE, NO MATTER
WHAT YOUR PARTY IS.
STAND UP AND SAY IN TODAY'S
WORD, WHEN ANTI-SEMITISM IS ON
THE RISE, WHEN WE HAVE THE
HISTORY THAT WE HAVE AND WE KNOW
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN PEOPLE REMAIN
SILENT, EVERY SINGLE ONE OF US
MUST AT ALL TIMES STAND AGAINST
IT.
>> THERE'S A COUPLE FOREIGN
POLICY HEADLINES.
THIS WAS THE PRESIDENT ON FRIDAY
ABOUT NORTH KOREA.
>> I HAVE A FEELING THAT OUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH NORTH KOREA,
KIM JONG-UN AND MYSELF, CHAIRMAN
KIM, I THINK IT'S A GOOD ONE.
AND I THINK IT REMAINS GOOD.
I WOULD BE SURPRISED IN A
NEGATIVE WAY IF HE DID ANYTHING
THAT WAS NOT PER OUR
UNDERSTANDING.
>> THIS IS WHAT WE LEARNED THIS
WEEK.
HE'S ACCELERATING THE ROCKET
PROGRAM AGAIN.
HE'S ENRICHED MORE URANIUM
BETWEEN THE TWO SUMMITS.
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY, THEY WERE
RECONSTITUTING THE PROGRAMS
WHILE THE SUMMIT -- SECOND
SUMMIT WAS TAKING PLACE.
THE PRESIDENT THERE.
YOU CAN'T TAKE HIM AT HIS WORD
ON THIS, CAN YOU?
>> WE HAVE WATCHED KIM JONG-UN
AND HIS FATHER AND HIS
GRANDFATHER OPERATE THE SAME
WAY, NOW, FOR DECADES.
AND I WOULD SAY THAT REPUBLICAN
AND DEMOCRATIC ADMINISTRATIONS
GOT TAKEN BY HIM.
I HOPE THIS PRESIDENT WON'T.
I THINK THAT, YOU KNOW, THEIR
EFFORTS ARE ABSOLUTELY CLEAR.
>> HASN'T HE GOTTEN MORE OUT OF
THIS PRESIDENT BY GETTING
RESPECT ON THE WORLD STAGE?
>> I THINK THE FACT THAT THE
PRESIDENT WALKED AWAY FROM THE
SUMMIT IN VIETNAM IS A POSITIVE
THING.
THAT WAS THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
WE DON'T WANT A BAD DEAL.
IT MAKES US LESS SAFE.
>> BEFORE I LET YOU GO, THE
PRESIDENT'S GOING TO ROLL OUT A
BUDGET AND THERE'S SOMETHING IN
THIS THAT'S GOING TO BE QUITE
ALARMING TO SOME ALLIES.
THE PRESIDENT WILL ADVOCATE,
PERHAPS, WHERE WE HAVE TROOPS
OVERSEAS, THINK JAPAN, SOUTH
KOREA, GERMANY, HE'S GOING TO
ASK FOR COST-PLUS 50.
ESSENTIALLY TAX COUNTRIES OVER
AND ABOVE WHERE WE HAVE BASES.
WHAT DOES THAT DO TO THE
DIPLOMACY FOR THIS COUNTRY?
>> I THINK IT WOULD BE
ABSOLUTELY DEVASTATING.
WE BENEFIT TREMENDOUSLY.
IF YOU LOOK AT THE LAST 70
YEARS, WE ARE ABLE TO BENEFIT
FROM THE PERSPECTIVE OF FREEDOM,
PROSPERITY, AND SAFETY BECAUSE
OF THE BASES AND OUR COOPERATION
WITH THE ALLIES.
THE NOTION THAT WE'RE GOING TO
CHARGE THEM COST PLUS 50 IS
WRONG HEADED AND IT WOULD BE
DAMAGING TO THE NATION.
>> YOU THINK YOUR REPUBLICAN
PARTY WILL SUPPORT THIS?
>> I WON'T.
>> BUT THE PARTY MIGHT?
>> WELL, I THINK IT'S GOING TO
BE VERY IMPORTANT FOR US TO MAKE
SURE THAT PEOPLE UNDERSTAND THE
DANGER THAT WILL DO TO OUR
RELATIONSHIPS AND TO OUR
FUNDAMENTAL SECURITY.
OUR SECURITY, WE'VE BEEN ABLE TO
PROTECT IT BECAUSE OF OUR
ALLIANCES AND BECAUSE WE HAVE
BEEN ABLE TO WORK WITH
COUNTRIES.
WE SHOULD NOT LOOK AT THIS THAT
WE NEED TO CHARGE THEM RENT FOR
THE PRIVILEGE OF HAVING OUR
FORCES THERE BECAUSE THAT DOES
US A HUGE BENEFIT, AS WELL.
>> CONGRESSWOMAN LIZ CHENEY,
THANK YOU FOR COMING ON.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, DEMOCRATS
ARE GOING THROUGH THE SAME
GROWING PAINS REPUBLICANS DID
WHEN THE TEA PARTY EMERGED.
IT'S HARD TO KEEP COMPETING
FACTIONS HAPPY.
>>> AND THE WAITING FOR BIDEN
CAMPAIGN.
THE PANEL IS NEXT.
So, we re-imagined the razor
with the new Gillette SkinGuard.
It has a unique guard
between the blades.
That's designed to reduce
irritation during the shave.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
Gillette.
If you want to know why people
sacrifice everything for love,
you have to start by asking...
Could listening to Audible
help you find the secret
to a stronger relationship?
Sometimes it doesn't take
anything at all for us...
Just say "Alexa,
give me my free Audible book,"
and your first
pick is on us.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
PANEL IS HERE.
PAT McCRORY, THE FOREMAN
GOVERNOR OF NORTH CAROLINA.
MARIA TERESA KUMAR, PRESIDENT OF
VOTO LATINO.
KASIE HUNT.
CAPITOL HILL NEWS CORRESPONDENT.
AND ROBERT COSTA, THE MODERATOR
OF "WASHINGTON WEEK" ON PBS.
KASIE, LET'S UNPACK THE HILL
BEFORE WE GET TO THE
PRESIDENTIAL RACE.
THE HILL DEBATE IS GOING TO
ANIMATE THE PRESIDENTIAL RACE.
LET ME PLAY NANCY PELOSI ON OMAR
FROM FRIDAY.
>> THE INCIDENT THAT HAPPENED
WAS, I DON'T THINK OUR COLLEAGUE
IS ANTI-SEMITIC.
I THINK SHE HAS A DIFFERENT
EXPERIENCE IN THE USE OF WORDS,
DOESN'T UNDERSTAND THAT SOME OF
THEM ARE FRAUGHT WITH MEANING
THAT SHE DIDN'T REALIZE.
BUT NONETHELESS, THAT WE HAD TO
ADDRESS.
>> I WILL SAY THIS, SPEAKER
PELOSI HAS GIVEN ME MY NEW
FAVORITE EXCUSE, SHE HAS A
DIFFERENT EXPERIENCE WITH THE
USE OF WORDS.
THAT IS EASILY ONE OF MY
FAVORITE NEW PHRASES.
THIS IS NOT EASY.
>> IT'S NOT EASY, CHUCK.
ONE THING IF YOU SPEAK WITH
MEMBERS OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY,
WHO ARE FRUSTRATED HOW THEIR
PARTY HANDLED THIS.
THERE ARE JEWISH AND NON-JEWISH
DEMOCRATS THAT ARE FRANKLY UPSET
THAT THIS RESOLUTION WAS AS
BROAD AS IT WAS.
THEY'LL SAY THIS IS THE THIRD
TIME THIS HAS HAPPENED.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S USED -- SHE SAID
ISRAEL WAS HYPNOTIZING THE WORLD
IN A TWEET BEFORE SHE WAS IN
OFFICE.
SHE HAD THE BENJAMINS TWEET THAT
YOU SHOWED THE AUDIENCE AT THE
TOP OF THE SHOW.
NOW, SHE HAS THIS.
EVERY SINGLE TIME SHE HAS PLED
IGNORANCE OF THESE TROPES.
BUT YOU KNOW THEY'RE TROPES FOR
A REASON.
SHE'S PICKING UP ON LANGUAGE
THAT IS ANTI-SEMITIC, QUITE
FRANKLY.
I THINK NANCY PELOSI IS DOING
WHAT SHE HAS VERY CAREFULLY
DONE, SINCE THIS NEW CAUCUS HAS
COME TOGETHER, WHICH IS TRY TO
VERY CAREFULLY THREAD THAT
NEEDLE AND TRY TO SEW THESE TWO
VERY DISPIRIT GENERATIONS
TOGETHER AND IT'S GETTING
HARDER.
>> BUT THERE'S ONLY SO MUCH
SPEAKER PELOSI CAN DO.
I MET WITH HOUSE DEMOCRATS,
SEASONED VETERANS OVER THE LAST
WEEK.
THEY SAID IN THIS DAY AND AGE OF
SOCIAL MEDIA, WHERE SOMEONE LIKE
REPRESENTATIVE OMAR OR
OCASIO-CORTEZ CAN HAVE
MILLIONS OF FOLLOWERS, THE OLD
RULES DON'T APPLY.
AND SO, SPEAKER PELOSI MAY TRY
TO COBBLE TOGETHER LEGISLATION,
TO SEND A MESSAGE TO VOTERS.
BUT THE PEOPLE WHO HAVE
POLITICAL CAPITAL INSIDE THIS
PARTY, ARE THOSE WITH A SOCIAL
MEDIA FOLLOWING.
>> OKAY.
IF YOU GET OFF SOCIAL MEDIA, THE
WORLD LOOKS NORMAL.
>> FAIRLY DIFFERENT.
>> BUT IF YOU LIVE ON SOCIAL
MEDIA -- I MEAN, I DON'T MEAN TO
CARRY THIS OVER.
THE NBA IS HAVING A PROBLEM.
ITS PLAYERS ARE MAKING ALL THIS
MONEY AND THEY'RE DEPRESSED
ALL THE TIME BECAUSE THEY LIVE
ON SOCIAL MEDIA AND FEEL EVERY
NEGATIVE COMMENT AND LIVE ALL OF
IT.
THAT'S WHAT IS HAPPENING TO THIS
YOUNGER GENERATION.
>> AND PART OF IT, TOO, IS YOU
DON'T KNOW WHO IS TWEETING YOU.
ARE THEY BOTS OR REAL PEOPLE?
WHEN IT COMES TO BASICALLY
FEELING THIS.
AND THE CHALLENGE IS, PRESIDENT
TRUMP HAS REALLY DONE A
FANTASTIC JOB, COMMUNICATING TO
A BROADER AUDIENCE BASED ON HIS
TWEETS.
AND IT'S TOE-TO-TOE WITH A
GENERATION THAT EXPECTS THEY'RE
GOING TO HAVE THEIR BREAKING
NEWS, NOT ON "THE NEW YORK
TIMES," BUT THROUGH A TWEET.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO HAVE THE
ACCURATE LITERACY IS THIS
ACTUALLY LITERATE?
THAT'S A CHALLENGE.
>> AS A FORMER MAYOR AND
GOVERNOR, I THOUGHT THAT
RESOLUTIONS WITHOUT ACTIONS WERE
EMPTY GESTURES.
AND THIS RESOLUTION WAS AN EMPTY
GESTURE, WHICH TRIED TO PLEASE
EVERYONE AND ENDED UP PLEASING
NO ONE.
BUT THE PROBLEM FOR THE
DEMOCRATS, WITH THESE NEW
MILLENNIALS, I CALL THEM THE AOC
MILLENNIALS, NOT ONLY DO THEY
THINK THEY HAVE THE ANSWERS,
THEY THINK THEY ALREADY HAVE
WISDOM.
AND THE NANCY PELOSI'S OF THE
WORLD HAVE WISDOM.
AND THEY ARE TRYING TO EXPLAIN
TO THE YOUNGER PEOPLE, WAIT, I'M
THE OLD PERSON.
AND YOU CANNOT MAKE THAT
ARGUMENT.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
BRING IT ON.
HERE YOU GO.
>> HONESTLY, I THINK THE LEADERS
CAN LEARN SOMETHING FROM THE
NEWER -- I TAKE YOUR POINT THAT,
YOU KNOW, THEY HAVE NOT HAD THE
KIND OF EXPERIENCE IN GOVERNMENT
AND I THINK TO A CERTAIN EXTENT,
THERE ARE GOING TO BE
CONSEQUENCES FOR SOME OF THE
ACTIONS THEY TAKE ON SOCIAL
MEDIA, IN THE UNIVERSE OF TRYING
TO GET THINGS DONE.
BUT ON THE OTHER HAND, I THINK
THE OLD GUARD DOESN'T REALLY
UNDERSTAND THE POWER OF WHAT
THEY BRING.
>> BY THE WAY, GUYS, I WANT TO
INSERT SOMEBODY INTO HERE REALLY
QUICKLY.
FIRST OF ALL, "THE TIMES" SET IT
UP REALLY WELL.
"THE TIMES" SAID, THIS IS A
DEBATE IN THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
DO AMERICANS PINE FOR A
PRE-TRUMP EQUILIBRIUM?
OR DO THE YAWNING DISPARITIES OF
THESE TIMES CALL OUT FOR A MORE
TRANSFORMATIONAL ADMINISTRATION?
>> THAT.
ABSOLUTELY THAT.
>> NOW, LISTEN TO AOC YESTERDAY.
LISTEN TO THIS.
>> MODERATE IS NOT A STANCE.
IT'S JUST AN ATTITUDE TOWARD
LIFE OF, LIKE --
THE MEH IS LIKE WORSHIPED NOW
FOR WHAT?
>> I REST MY CASE.
BUT THE POINT I WANT TO MAKE IS
THERE'S ANOTHER ISSUE THAT
BROUGHT OUT THE AOC MILLENNIALS
AGAINST THE TRADITIONAL LIBERAL
DEMOCRATS.
THAT WAS AMAZON.
CUOMO, ONE OF THE MOST LIBERAL
MAYORS OF NEW YORK CITY WE'VE
EVER HAD, GAVE TAX BREAKS TO A
MAJOR MULTIBILLION DOLLAR
COMPANY AND AOC FOUGHT IT.
SHE SAID, WE CAN SPEND THAT
$2 BILLION ELSEWHERE.
THE $2 BILLION DIDN'T EXIST.
SHE DIDN'T HAVE THE KNOWLEDGE
NECESSARY OF THE ECONOMY.
NOW, PHILOSOPHY, THAT'S A GOOD
ARGUMENT.
THAT'S ALSO SHOWING THE DIVISION
IN THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
>> I THINK THAT WHAT MILLENNIALS
ARE FEELING IS THEY ARE FEELING
FROM THEIR EXPERIENCE.
THEY KNOW THAT SOMETHING IS OFF.
THEY KNOW THEIR EXPERIENCE THAT
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE A
GUARANTEED BRIGHTER FUTURE THAN
THEIR PARENTS IS NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN.
>> IT'S BROKEN.
>> THE COMPACT IS BROKEN.
IT USED TO BE IF YOU WORKED
HARD AND YOU FOLLOWED THE ETHICS
OF YOUR PARENTS, YOU WOULD END
UP WORKING FOR A COMPANY THAT
WOULD TAKE CARE OF YOU FOR A
LONG TIME.
THAT'S NOT THE CASE ANYMORE.
IT IS SIMPLY NOT THE CASE.
>> IT'S BIGGER THAN AGE.
THE POINT REPRESENTATIVE CORTEZ
IS MAKING, IS THAT THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY NEEDS TO MOVE
TO THE LEFT.
YOU LOOK AT THIS 2020
PRESIDENTIAL RACE, WHERE IS THE
ENERGY?
FUND-RAISING, BERNIE SANDERS.
CROWDS, SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS.
HE'S IN HIS UPPER 70s.
YET, HE'S THE RUNNER-UP FROM '16
AND HE'S SAYING TO PEOPLE LIKE
THE REPRESENTATIVE OF NEW YORK,
I'M YOUR TYPE OF CANDIDATE.
I'M NOT A MEH CANDIDATE, TO USE
HER TERM.
>> IT TAKES TWO 75-PLUS-YEAR-OLD
GUYS TO HAVE AN ARGUMENT BETWEEN
THIS GENERATIONAL ARGUMENT HERE.
ARE THEY PLACE HOLDERS FOR NOW
UNTIL THE YOUNGER GENERATION
GETS MORE GRASS ROOTS SUPPORT?
>> I THINK THAT EVERYBODY IS
WAITING IN THE WINGS IN LARGE
PART BECAUSE THEY ARE WAITING
FOR BETO TO ANNOUNCE.
UNLIKE ALL OF THE OTHER
DEMOCRATS THAT ARE TRYING TO
MOVE AS FAR TO THE LEFT TO SAY
YEAH, I'M YOUR PERSON, HE HAS
NOT NECESSARILY SAID THAT HE IS.
AND HE'S MORE PALATABLE TO THE
INDEPENDENTS.
AND HE'S DONE THAT IN AN
INTERESTING WAY.
IF YOU ASK HIM WHERE HIS
POLICIES ARE, THEY'RE NOT ON THE
LEFT.
>> ALL THINGS TO ALL PEOPLE.
>> IF THERE'S A CRITICISM ON
BETO, YOU DON'T KNOW WHERE HE
STANDS ON A LOT OF THINGS.
IF YOU READ HIS INTERVIEWS.
>> ALL OF THE LEFT-WING STANCES,
THE GREEN PLAN, WHERE THE
MILLENNIALS REALIZE THEY HAVE TO
HAVE ENERGY AND POWER AT AN
AFFORDABLE PRICE, THEY WILL FIND
OUT THAT ENERGY IS NOT CHEAP.
YOU NEED ENERGY TO SURVIVE.
AND THE REALITY IS GOING TO WAKE
THEM UP SOME TIME.
>> THIS IS A CONVERSATION THAT
NEEDS MORE TIME.
AND I'M GOING TO GIVE IT MORE
TIME.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, PRESIDENT
TRUMP SAYS MICHAEL COHEN IS
LYING ABOUT ASKING FOR A PARDON.
COHEN SAYS IT'S MR. TRUMP WHO IS
LYING.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT DOES ADAM SCHIFF THINK
BECAUSE MICHAEL COHEN HAS LIED
TO HIM, TOO.
THE CHAIRMAN OF THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE JOINS ME
NEXT.
EE JOINS ME
NEXT
New Olay Clay Stick Masks,
Hydrating Facial Mist,
And Brightening Eye Cream.
Only by Olay.
I'm a dancer,
I live in New York City.
Casting directors will send me
a video of choreography
and say, "If you can be here
in a couple hours,
the job is yours."
And then I need my phone to work
while I'm on the subway,
or streaming
the video they sent me
while I learn the choreography
as best I can.
They key is to hold
the bar up top and not the pole,
so that you have
full range of motion.
It's a little kooky.
(chuckles)
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now comes with
Apple Music on us.
Get a free Galaxy S10e
when you buy the new Galaxy S10.
Termites,
feasting on homes 24/7.
Only on Verizon.
We're on the move.
Roger.
Hey Rick, all good?
Oh yeah, we're good.
We're good.
Termites never stop trying to
get in,
we never stop working to keep
them out.
Terminix.
Defenders of Home.
THIS BED.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
THIS WAS A WEEK IN WHICH WE SAW
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S FORMER
CAMPAIGN CHAIRMAN PAUL MANAFORT
GET SENTENCED TO PRISON.
THINK ABOUT THAT FOR A MOMENT.
THE MAN WHO MADE SURE DONALD
TRUMP SECURED THE DOMINATION FOR
THE PRESIDENCY, WAS SENTENCED TO
47 MONTHS IN PRISON WITH
SENTENCING IN ANOTHER CASE
COMING THIS WEEK.
WE SAW MR. TRUMP AND COHEN CALL
EACH OTHER A LIAR, OVER WHETHER
COHEN SOUGHT A PARDON FROM THE
PRESIDENT.
A LOT TO CHEW ON.
WE'RE GOING TO TURN TO ADAM
SCHIFF, WHO JOINS ME FROM LOS
ANGELES.
AND ON SPRING-FORWARD DAY I'M
GRATEFUL FOR YOU GETTING UP THAT
HOUR EARLIER.
CONGRESSMAN SCHIFF, WELCOME BACK
TO "MEET THE PRESS," SIR.
>> THANK YOU.
>> LET ME START WITH A BASIC
QUESTION HERE.
WHO IS LYING?
WHEN IT COMES TO MICHAEL COHEN
ASKED FOR A PARDON.
AND DID MICHAEL COHEN LIE TO
CONGRESS AGAIN?
>> WELL, THE CENTRAL QUESTION OF
OUR INVESTIGATION IS, WHY DID
MICHAEL COHEN LIE BEFORE OUR
COMMITTEE ABOUT MOSCOW TRUMP
TOWER?
WHY WOULD THIS BE IN HIS
INTEREST?
WAS THIS SOMETHING THAT HE DID
ALONE OR WERE THERE OTHERS
INVOLVED IN IT?
AND THERE ARE REASONS TO BELIEVE
THAT THIS WAS NOT A LONE
DECISION ON MICHAEL COHEN.
WHAT WE ARE LOOKING FOR IS
CORROBORATIVE EVIDENCE.
AND THE REASON WHY THIS WHOLE
MOSCOW TRUMP TOWER ISSUE IS SO
CENTRAL TO OUR INVESTIGATION IS,
THAT IT EXPLAINS OR POTENTIALLY
EXPLAINS THE PRESIDENT'S BIZARRE
AFFINITY FOR VLADIMIR PUTIN.
AND THAT IS, HE STOOD TO MAKE
MORE MONEY FROM THIS TRANSACTION
THAN ANY DEAL IN HIS LIFE.
AND SOUGHT THE KREMLIN'S HELP TO
MAKE THIS HAPPEN WHILE
CONCEALING THIS FROM THE PUBLIC.
THAT MAY BE AN ANIMATED
PRINCIPLE FOR THE PRESIDENT.
HE MAY BELIEVE THAT WHEN HE
LEAVES OFFICE, HE STILL WANTS TO
BUILD THIS TOWER.
AND WHILE THAT MAY NOT BE
CRIMINAL, IT IS NONETHELESS
CORRUPT AND DISTORTS OUR
POLICIES.
THAT IS CERTAINLY THE CENTRAL
QUESTION FOR US.
IN TERMS OF WHO IS TELLING THE
TRUTH BETWEEN MICHAEL COHEN AND
THE PRESIDENT, WE KNOW THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAS MADE PROBABLY OVER
1,000 FALSE STATEMENTS ABOUT THE
RUSSIA ISSUES.
AND HERE, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
FIND WHAT CORROBORATION WE CAN
TO FIND OUT WHERE THE TRUTH
LIES.
>> IS IT SAFE TO SAY YOU CAN'T
TAKE MICHAEL COHEN ON HIS WORD
ON ANYTHING?
>> I DON'T THINK IN TERMS OF
MAKING THE CASE TO THE PUBLIC --
AND HERE, WE'RE NOT MAKING THE
CASE TO A JURY ABOUT WHAT TOOK
PLACE ON THAT WEEKEND AND RELY
SOLELY ON THE TESTIMONY OF
MICHAEL COHEN.
WE'RE GOING TO NEED
CORROBORATION.
LOOKING AT WHAT MICHAEL COHEN
SAID IN THE OPEN HEARING AND
WHAT HIS LAWYER SAID AFTERWARDS,
IT WAS LIKE WHAT DONALD TRUMP
DID WHEN HE SAID HE HAD NO
KNOWLEDGE OF THE PAYMENTS TO
STORMY DANIELS.
AND RUDY GIULIANI SAID, OH, YES,
HE DID.
WHERE IS THE TRUTH THERE?
WE ASKED MICHAEL COHEN ABOUT
THIS EXTENSIVELY.
THOSE TRANSCRIPTS WILL BE MADE
PUBLIC.
THE PUBLIC CAN EVALUATE HIS
CREDIBILITY THEMSELVES.
>> YOU KNOW, IT LOOKS LIKE WE
DON'T KNOW THIS FOR SURE, BUT IT
LOOKS LIKE ROBERT MUELLER WILL
COMPLETE HIS INVESTIGATION
WITHOUT SUBPOENAING THE
PRESIDENT BEFORE THE GRAND JURY
OR COMING UP WITH A WAY TO HAVE
HIM INTERVIEWED BEFORE THE GRAND
JURY.
PRESIDENT CLINTON WENT BEFORE
KEN STARR'S GRAND JURY.
IF, INDEED, MR. MUELLER DECIDES
NOT TO ISSUE THAT SUBPOENA OR
FIGURE OUT HOW TO GET THE
PRESIDENT IN FRONT OF THAT GRAND
JURY, IS THAT GOING TO HAVE BEEN
A MISTAKE, CONSIDERING WE HAVE
SO MANY QUESTIONS ABOUT WHO'S
TESTIMONY SHOULD YOU BELIEVE?
MICHAEL COHEN'S OR DONALD
TRUMP'S?
>> YES, I THINK IT IS A MISTAKE.
I SAID ALL ALONG THAT I DON'T
THINK BOB MUELLER SHOULD RELY ON
WRITTEN ANSWERS.
WHEN YOU GET WRITTEN ANSWERS
FROM A WITNESS, IT'S REALLY THE
LAWYERS' ANSWERS AS MUCH AS THE
CLIENT'S ANSWER.
YOU NEED TO BE ABLE TO ASK
FOLLOW-UP QUESTIONS IN
REALTIME.
BUT I THINK THE CONSTRAINT THAT
BOB MUELLER IS OPERATING UNDER,
HE HAD AN ACTING ATTORNEY
GENERAL WHO WAS APPOINTED
BECAUSE HE WOULD BE HOSTILE TO A
SUBPOENA ON THE PRESIDENT.
AND NOW, HE HAS A PERMANENT
ATTORNEY GENERAL WHO WAS CHOSEN
FOR THE SAME HOSTILITY TO HIS
INVESTIGATION, WHO WOULD LIKELY
OPPOSE THAT STEP.
I ALSO THINK THE SPECIAL COUNSEL
FEELS SOME TIME PRESSURE TO
CONCLUDE HIS WORK AND KNOWING
THE WHITE HOUSE WOULD DRAG OUT A
FIGHT OVER THE SUBPOENA.
THAT MAY BE AN ISSUE, AS WELL.
I THINK ULTIMATELY IT'S A
MISTAKE BECAUSE PROBABLY THE
BEST WAY TO GET THE TRUTH WOULD
BE TO PUT THE PRESIDENT UNDER
OATH.
AS HE'S MADE PLAIN IN THE PAST,
HE FEELS IT'S FINE TO LIE TO THE
PUBLIC AFTER ALL HE HAS SAID,
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M TALKING BEFORE
A MAGISTRATE.
MAYBE HE SHOULD TALK BEFORE
A IMAGE STRAIGHT.
>> I WANT TO MOVE TO SOMETHING
THAT WAS A BIT CONFUSING.
ERIK PRINCE, THE BROTHER OF THE
SECRETARY OF EDUCATION, BUT ALSO
HAS BEEN BEFORE YOUR COMMITTEE,
HAVING TO DO WITH SOME ODD
MEETINGS HE SET UP IN THE
SEYCHELLES.
HE WAS ON AL-JAZEERA AND HE WAS
ASKED ABOUT SOME TESTIMONY TO
YOUR COMMITTEE AND ABOUT WHETHER
HE LIED OR NOT.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> WE'RE THERE TO TALK ABOUT
IRAN POLICY.
>> THERE TO TALK ABOUT IRAN
POLICY?
ISN'T THAT IMPORTANT TO DISCLOSE
TO THE HOUSE COMMITTEE UNDER
OATH?
>> I DID.
>> THERE'S NO MENTION OF THE
TRUMP TOWER MEETING IN 2016.
WHY NOT?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF THEY GOT THE
TRANSCRIPT WRONG.
>> SO, THIS WAS ABOUT ANOTHER
MEETING THAT ERIK PRINCE HAD, I
BELIEVE WITH SOME OTHER
REPRESENTATIVES OF OTHER
COUNTRIES, IN TRUMP TOWER, THE
SECOND SO-CALLED TRUMP TOWER
MEETING OF LESS SIGNIFICANCE,
NOT WITH RUSSIANS BUT WITH OTHER
FOREIGN COUNTRIES.
BASED ON WHAT YOU HEARD THERE,
IS MR. PRINCE TELLING THE TRUTH?
IS YOUR TRANSCRIPT WRONG?
>> HE'S NOT TELLING THE TRUTH ON
THAT INTERVIEW.
THERE IS SOMETHING WRONG WITH
OUR TRANSCRIPT.
THERE WAS NOTHING WRONG WITH THE
REPORTER WHO TRANSCRIBED HIS
TESTIMONY.
HE DID NOT DISCLOSE THAT MEETING
TO OUR COMMITTEE.
AND AS YOU CAN SEE FROM THE
PUBLISHED TRANSCRIPT OF HIS
INTERVIEW, HE WAS ASKED WHAT
KIND OF ROLE HE PLAYED, IF ANY,
IN THE CAMPAIGN, AND HE SAID HE
HAD NO ROLE, APART FROM ON HIS
OWN SUBMITTING WRITTEN PAPERS,
HANGING A YARD SIGN OR MAKING A
CONTRIBUTION.
AND HE WAS ALSO ASKED ABOUT ANY
SUBSTANTIVE POLICY CONVERSATIONS
THAT HE MIGHT HAVE HAD.
SO, HIS INTERVIEW WAS CERTAINLY
LOOKS INCONSISTENT WITH HIS
TESTIMONY.
BOB MUELLER HAS THAT TESTIMONY
ALREADY.
AND BOB MUELLER WILL HAVE TO
MAKE THE DECISION ABOUT WHETHER
THAT RISES TO THE LEVEL OF
DELIBERATE FALSEHOOD.
WE HAD QUESTIONS AT THE TIME OF
HIS TESTIMONY ABOUT HIS CANDOR
AND HOW FORTHCOMING HE WAS AND
THOSE QUESTIONS HAVE BEEN
HEIGHTENED NOW.
>> WHAT IS YOUR CONCERN ABOUT
WHAT HE WAS DOING?
>> THE CONCERN IS THAT THIS IS
ANOTHER CONCEALED MEETING.
ANOTHER DISCUSSION THAT TOOK
PLACE IN THE CONTEXT OF THE
MEETING THAT HE HAD IN THE
SEYCHELLES.
THERE HAVE BEEN PERSISTENT
QUESTIONS ABOUT WHETHER THE UAE
WAS PLAYING A BACK CHANNEL ROLE
TO THE RUSSIANS DURING THE
CAMPAIGN.
AND THOSE WERE A LOT OF THE
QUESTIONS THAT WE WERE ASKING
HIM ABOUT.
CLEARLY, THIS MEETING AT TRUMP
TOWER WITH THESE PLAYERS, WAS OF
DIRECT INTEREST TO OUR
COMMITTEE.
SO, WHY CONCEAL IT?
WHY WITHHOLD THAT INFORMATION IF
THERE WAS NOTHING IMPROPER, NO
IMPROPER PURPOSE IN IT?
THERE ARE A LOT OF DEEPLY
CONCERNING AND UNANSWERED
QUESTIONS SURROUNDING ERIK
PRINCE AND HIS INVOLVEMENT WITH
THE CAMPAIGN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ADAM SCHIFF, I WILL LEAVE IT
THERE.
THE DEMOCRATIC LEAD ON THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE, THE
CHAIRMAN.
THANKS VERY MUCH FOR COMING ON,
GETTING UP EARLY AND SHARING
YOUR VIEWS WITH US THIS MORNING.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE STATE
THE DEMOCRATS HAVE ON THEIR
MINDS FOR 2020.
COULD IT BE THE GAME CHANGER
THAT GETS THEM OVER 270?
We humans are
strange creatures.
Other species avoid pain
And struggle.
We actually... seek it out.
Other species do
difficult things
Because they have to.
We do difficult things.
Because we like to.
We think it's... fun.
Introducing the all-new
2019 Ford Ranger
Built for the strangest
of all creatures.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
"DATA DOWNLOAD" TIME.
HEADING INTO THE 2020 ELECTION,
DEMOCRATS ARE EXCITED ABOUT THE
OPPORTUNITY FOR AN ELECTORAL
PICKUP.
IT'S NOT TEXAS.
IT'S NOT ARIZONA.
BUT GEORGIA.
THAT'S RIGHT.
A STATE THAT HASN'T VOTED FOR A
DEMOCRAT FOR PRESIDENT SINCE
BILL CLINTON IN 1992.
LET'S LOOK TO COBB COUNTY, WHAT
A SUBURB OF ATLANTA.
NEWT GINGRICH REPRESENTED AND
THE RAPIDLY CHANGING POLITICS IN
THE LAST FEW YEARS.
IN 2012, COBB COUNTY VOTED FOR
REPUBLICAN MITT ROMNEY FOR
PRESIDENT FOR A WHOPPING 12
POINTS.
FOUR YEARS LATER IT SWUNG TO
HILLARY CLINTON AND SHE WON THE
COUNTY BY TWO POINTS.
BEFORE YOU SAY, THAT'S JUST A
DONALD TRUMP ANOMALY, REALIZE
THAT THIS PAST NOVEMBER, STACEY
ABRAMS, THE DEMOCRATIC
CANDIDATE FOR GOVERNOR WON COBB
COUNTY BY NEARLY TEN POINTS.
SO A 22 POINT SWING IN JUST SIX
YEARS.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE WENT DOWN TO COBB COUNTY TO
FIGURE IT OUT.
>> IT'S CHANGING IN COBB COUNTY.
IT WAS ONCE MORE REPUBLICANS.
NOW, WE HAVE A LOT OF MOVE-INS
AND IT'S GETTING A MIXTURE NOW.
GEORGIA IS BECOMING A MIXTURE.
YOU KNOW?
I SORT OF LIKE THE REPUBLICAN
PART OF IT.
>> IT'S TRUE.
COBB COUNTY HAS SEEN A TON OF
PEOPLE MOVE IN THE LAST FEW
YEARS.
BETWEEN 2010 AND 2017, COBB
COUNTY'S POPULATION GREW 9.8%,
OUTPACING GROWTH IN GEORGIA AS A
WHOLE.
IN THAT SAME TIME, COBB COUNTY
HAS GROWN MORE DIVERSE.
WITH INCREASES TO THE
AFRICAN-AMERICAN AND HISPANIC
POPULATIONS.
MORE RESIDENTS HAVE COLLEGE
DEGREES AND MEDIAN HOUSEHOLD
INCOME HAS GONE FROM $66,000 TO
$72,000 PER YEAR.
THE MORE TELLING DATA MAY BE
WHERE THE TRANSPLANTS TO COBB
COUNTY ARE COMING FROM.
OF THE TOP 20 COUNTIES THAT
PEOPLE MOVE TO COBB FROM, SINCE
2012, 13 ARE FROM OUTSIDE THE
STATE OF GEORGIA.
AND 15 OF THOSE COUNTIES VOTED
FOR HILLARY CLINTON, INCLUDING
QUEENS, NEW YORK, L.A. COUNTY
AND MIAMI-DADE.
THIS IS JUST COBB COUNTY, OF
COURSE.
BUT YOU CAN SEE A LOT OF THE
CHANGES IN THE OTHER SUBURBAN
COUNTIES, WHERE THE VOTE HAS
ALSO SWUNG TOWARDS THE DEMOCRATS
IN AND AROUND ATLANTA.
SO, IS GEORGIA READY TO BE A
SWING STATE AGAIN?
>> THE YOUNGER CROWD IS
DEFINITELY GOING TO GO TOWARDS
THIS.
>> I HAVE NO DOUBT THAT A
PROGRESSIVE CANDIDATE CAN WIN
STATEWIDE.
>> I THINK GEORGIA HAS BEEN A
SWING STATE BEFORE.
I THINK IT'S MOVING TOWARDS THAT
WAY AGAIN.
>> I CAN'T IMAGINE NOT BEING A
RED STATE.
I REALLY CAN'T.
>> WE'LL FIND OUT SOON ENOUGH.
>>> COMING UP, PAUL MANAFORT, A
CONTROVERSIAL SENTENCE AND THAT
CLAIM THAT HE'S LIVED AN
OTHERWISE BLAMELESS LIFE.
arthri,
month after month,
the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
HUMIRA can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
HUMIRA targets and blocks
a source of inflammation
that contributes
to joint pain
and irreversible damage.
VO: HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections
including tuberculosis,
and cancers, including
lymphoma, have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Woman:
Help stop the clock
on further irreversible
joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here. Right now.
HUMIRA.
Discover.
Hi, what's this
Social Security Alert?
It's a free alert if
we find your Social
Security number on the dark web.
Good, cuz I'm a little
worried about
my information getting out.
Why's that?
[bird speaking]
My social is 8- 7- 5 dash
Okay, I see.
[bird laughing]
SOMEBODY thinks it's hilarious.
Free Social Security
Alerts from Discover.
PROTECT, CONNECT
>>> BACK,  NOW WITH END GAME.
DES MOINES REGISTER WITH THE
DEMOCRATIC DIVIDE.
WE SHOULD HURRY UP AND GET A
POLL IN HERE.
LET ME PUT UP THE DES MOINES
REGISTER POLL.
MEANINGFUL AND M
AT THE SAME TIME.
WE SEE WHO THE TOP TWO
CANDIDATES ARE, BIDEN AND
SANDERS.
WARREN AT 9, AND HARRIS AT 7,
RIGHT BELOW HARRIS IS BETO AT 5.
BOOKER AND KLOBUCHAR, OVER 1%.
WHAT IS TELLING THERE, YOU CAN
TELL THAT BUZZ IS EVERYTHING.
BERNIE'S NUMBERS WENT UP SIX
POINTS FROM THE LAST TIME.
AND WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN THIS TIME AND THE LAST
TIME?
BERNIE IS IN THE MIDDLE OF AN
ANNOUNCEMENT TOUR.
>> AND SANDERS IS RUNNING AS A
MOVEMENT POLITICIAN.
HE'S GOTTEN RID OF HIS
CONSULTANTS.
HE'S BUILT A MOVEMENT FROM HIS
2016 CAMPAIGN.
AND SENATOR WARREN HAS A
MESSAGE.
BREAK UP THE BIG COMPANIES, GO
AFTER TECH.
IT'S A CROWDED SPACE ON THAT
LEFT SIDE OF THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY.
>> YOU KNOW, CHUCK, ONE OF THE
MOST INTERESTING THINGS IN THAT
POLL, IF YOU LOOK AT THE NUMBERS
FOR BIDEN, THE BIGGEST CHUNK OF
THEM, IF YOU ASK WHO THE SECOND
CHOICE IS, THE ANSWER IS BERNIE
SANDERS, WHICH IS PRETTY
REMARKABLE.
I DO THINK --
>> I THOUGHT SO, TOO.
THEY'RE THE MAINSTREAM OF THE
PARTY, THE TWO OF THEM TOGETHER.
>> POTENTIALLY, YES.
AND BERNIE SANDERS' FUND-RAISING
MEANS THAT HE IS GOING TO BE A
FACTOR.
HE HAS A CORE OF SUPPORTERS.
I'M NOT SURE IT'S BIG ENOUGH TO
WIN HIM BIG STATES.
BUT IF HE POLLS 20%, 25%
CONSISTENTLY, HE WILL HAVE THE
MONEY TO GO THE DISTANCE.
MARK MY WORDS, YOU WILL SEE HIM
AT THE CONVENTION.
>> BERNIE SANDERS IS ONE OF THE
FEW PEOPLE, HE NEVER STOPS
CAMPAIGNING.
HE DOES FACEBOOK LIVES WHERE HE
HAS 30,000 PEOPLE WATCHING AND
FOLLOWING HIM.
HE REALLY APPEALS TO YOUNG
VOTERS.
FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME YOUNG
VOTERS ARE GOING TO OUTWEIGH,
POTENTIALLY, THE MILLENNIALS --
EXCUSE ME, THE BABY BOOMERS.
THEY WILL HAVE MORE ELIGIBLE
VOTERS.
>> THEREFORE, I WOULD LIKE TO
APOLOGIZE AND DO A RESOLUTION,
BASED ON WHAT I SAID ABOUT THE
MILLENNIALS.
I WOULD LIKE TO SAY THIS, THE
MORE THE CANDIDATES GET OUT,
WE'LL SEE TRUMP NUMBERS GO UP
BECAUSE THERE'S GOING TO BE A
COMPARISON.
IT'S ALREADY HAPPENING.
AND THE MORE CONGRESSMAN SCHIFF
TALKS ABOUT INVESTIGATIONS, AND
CONTINUING THESE INVESTIGATIONS,
AFTER THE MUELLER REPORT, I
THINK TRUMP NUMBERS WILL GO UP.
I THINK THE DEMOCRATS ARE GOING
TO PUT TRUMP IN OFFICE.
>> SPEAKING OF THE PRESIDENT, I
WANT TO PLAY WHAT HE SAID ABOUT
PAUL MANAFORT BECAUSE THERE'S A
PART OF THE EMPATHY I REALLY
DON'T GET WHEN IT COMES TO
BECOME THE SITTING PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> I FEEL VERY BADLY FOR PAUL
MANAFORT.
I THINK IT'S BEEN A VERY, VERY
TOUGH TIME FOR HIM.
BUT IF YOU NOTICE, BOTH HIS
LAWYER, A HIGHLY RESPECTED MAN,
AND A HIGHLY RESPECTED JUDGE,
THE JUDGE, SAID THERE WAS NO
COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA.
>> WELL, THE JUDGE DID NOT SAY
THAT, THOUGH THE JUDGE DID SAY
THIS ABOUT MANAFORT, I THINK
THIS SENTENCING RANGE IS
EXCESSIVE.
HE'S BEEN A GOOD FRIEND TO
OTHERS.
WHAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND IS WHY
THE PRESIDENT IS PRAISING AND
FEELING SORRY FOR A MAN WHO
DEFRAUDED AMERICAN TAXPAYERS FOR
AT LEAST $6 MILLION.
>> YOU KNOW WHO ELSE WONDERS
THAT?
MANY TRUMP ADVISERS.
THEY WISH THE PRESIDENT WOULD BE
QUIET ABOUT PAUL MANAFORT.
THEY WISH JUDGE ELLIS OF
ALEXANDRIA WOULD BE THEIR
SPOKESMAN.
>> COULD HAVE BEEN.
>> HE IS MAKING THE BEST CASE
FOR THIS ADMINISTRATION.
THE DEPUTY CHIEF OF STAFF OUT AS
THE COMMUNICATIONS HEAD.
THE PRESIDENT GOING ON AND ON,
TALKING ABOUT POSSIBLE PARDONS.
THEY WISH ALL OF THAT WOULD JUST
BE NOISE.
IT'S TELL LIS CASE, DIMINISHING
THE MUELLER PROBE.
THAT'S WHAT THE WHITE HOUSE
WANTS.
>> THERE'S A VIDEO RIGHT NOW, OF
A WHALE ALMOST SWALLOWING A
PERSON SWIMMING IN THE OCEAN.
AND HE SPITS HIM OUT.
TRUMP NEEDS TO SPIT MANAFORT
OUT.
AND THE CHAIRMAN OF THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE NEEDS TO
GET RID OF COHEN.
STAY AWAY FROM BOTH OF THEM.
THEY'RE NOT GOOD FOR EITHER
PARTY.
>> I THINK WE NEED TO CLARIFY
THAT WHAT HE WAS GETTING
SENTENCED FOR WAS RUSSIAN
COLLUSION.
>> IT WAS RIPPING OFF THE
AMERICAN GOVERNMENT OF 30 YEARS
OF LOBBYING.
>> ONE OF THE CONVERSATIONS THAT
PEOPLE ARE HAVING IS HOW UNJUST
THE SENTENCE WAS FOR THIS CRIME.
IF WE LOOK AT THIS JUDGE, THIS
JUDGE THREW THE BOOK AT
REPRESENTATIVE JEFFERSON FROM
LOUISIANA.
>> AN AFRICAN-AMERICAN DEMOCRAT
FROM NEW ORLEANS.
>> HE WAS FOUND TO HAVE
EMBEZZLED $400,000.
>> THE FREEZER CASUAL.
>> THE FREEZER CASH.
>> IT WAS SO MUCH LOWER THAN
WHAT PAUL MANAFORT IS DEALING
WITH.
>> IS THERE A JUSTICE WHEN IT
COMES TO WHITE COLLAR CRIME.
HE WAS TEETERING ON TREASON WHEN
IT COMES TO THIS.
WAS THAT FAIR?
THAT'S WHERE WE HAVE TO UNPACK
THE SENTENCE THAT HE WAS GIVEN.
>> THERE'S MORE SENTENCING
COMING FOR MR. MANAFORT.
THE SPINAL TAP DRUMMER
COMMISSION AT THE WHITE HOUSE --
I MEAN THE COMMUNICATIONS
DIRECTOR POSITION AT THE WHITE
HOUSE --
>> THERE'S SOME INSIGHT.
I LOVE IT.
>> HE BROUGHT UP BILL SHINE.
>> YOU WANT TO BE THE
COMMUNICATION DIRECTOR?
>> WHAT DOES THIS MEAN, KASIE?
>> TO BOB'S EARLIER POINT, WE'RE
GOING TO SEE MORE OF THE SAME.
YOU KNOW, I CERTAINLY WOULDN'T
WANT TO BE THE PERSON THAT NEEDS
TO TELL THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES HOW TO COMMUNICATE
WITH THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
GOOD LUCK.
HE'S BEEN DOING IT HIS ENTIRE
LIFE.
>> HOW MUCH DID "THE NEW YORKER"
PIECE HAVE TO DO WITH SHINE'S
RELEASE?
>> THE PRESIDENT WAS FRUSTRATED
WITH BILL SHINE, NOT BRINGING
THE FOX NEWS EXPERTISE.
MOST REVEALING OF THE MOST
RECENT WEEKS, PRESIDENT TRUMP AT
CPAC, TWO HOURS.
>> VOLUME AT 11 FOR PRESIDENT
TRUMP DURING THE SPEECH.
>> THAT'S ALL I HAVE FOR TODAY.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
THANK YOU FOR SPRINGING FORWARD
WITH US.
WE'LL BE BACK NEXT WEEK BECAUSE
IF IT'S SUNDAY, NO MATTER THE
HOUR, IT'S "MEET THE PRESS."
I've always been amazed
by what's next.
And still going for my best,
even though I live with
a higher risk of stroke
due to Afib not caused by
a heart valve problem.
So if there's a better treatment
than warfarin...
I want that too.
ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS is proven
to reduce stroke risk
better than warfarin.
Plus has significantly less
major bleeding than warfarin.
ELIQUIS is FDA-approved
and has both.
What's next?
Reeling in a nice one.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS
unless your doctor tells you to,
as stopping increases your risk
of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS If you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily
and it may take longer than
usual for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden sign of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase your
bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor
about all planned medical
or dental procedures.
ELIQUIS, the number one
cardiologist-prescribed
blood thinner.
Ask your doctor if ELIQUIS
is what's next for you.
Guys do whatever it takes to
deal with shave irritation.
So, we re-imagined the razor
with the new Gillette SkinGuard.
It has a unique guard
between the blades.
That's designed to reduce
irritation during the shave.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
Gillette.
I don't keep
track of regrets.
And I don't add
up the years.
But what I do count on...
is BOOST®
Delicious BOOST® High
Protein Nutritional Drink
has 20 grams of protein,
along with 26 essential
vitamins and minerals.
BOOST® High Protein.
Be Up for Life.