>>> THAT IS ALL FOR TONIGHT.
WILL BE BACK TOMORROW WITH
MORE "MTP DAILY."
"THE BEAT WITH ARI MELBER" START
S RIGHT NOW.
>>> A LOT OF STORIES ON "THE
BEAT" TONIGHT.
NANCY PELOSI MAKING THE NEWS,
DECLARING HER STANDARD TONIGHT
FOR WHAT IT WOULD TAKE TO
IMPEACH PRESIDENT TRUMP.
SHE SAYS, QUOTE, THIS IS NE.
I'M GOING TO BE JOINED LIVE BY
ONE OF HER TOP LIEUTENANTS ON
THAT UNFOLDING STORY FROM THE
HILL.
>>> LATER, AN INSIDER SPEAKS OUT
ON THE STORMY DANIELS HUSH MONEY
PAYMENTS AND CORROBORATING PARTS
OF MICHAEL COHEN'S ALLEGATIONS
AGAINST TRUMP.
>>> ALSO, MORE NEWS ON THE
CAMPAIGN FROM ELIZABETH WARREN,
INCLUDING SOME OF THE NEWS SHE
BROKE RIGHT HERE ON THIS SHOW ON
FRIDAY.
>>> BUT WE BEGIN WITH BOB
MUELLER GRINDING DOWN TWO FORMER
TRUMP AIDES.
THIS IS A PIVOTAL WEEK IN THE
MUELLER PROBE.
YOU'VE GOT ONE FEDERAL JUDGE WHO
WILL ISSUE RULINGSHAT WILL
DEFINE THE FATE AND POSSIBLY THE
FREEDOM OF BOTH ROGER STONE AND
PAUL MANAFORT, TWO FORMER TRUMP
AIDES WHO'VE ALSO WORKED
TOGETHER FOR DECADES.
AND IT'S THROUGH THEIR WORK ON
BEHALF OF DONALD TRUMP THAT BOTH
MEN ARE NOW IN POSITION.
THEY BOTH AWAIT RULINGS FROM AMY
BERMAN JACKSON.
SHE IS KNOWN AS A PRETTY TOUGH
FEDERAL JUDGE.
SHE IS THE ONE WHO FIRST CRACKED
DOWN ON MANAFORT, PUTTING HIM IN
JAIL OBVIOUSLY BEFORE HIS TRIAL.
OBVISLY A TOUGHER TACK THAN
THE OTHER FEDERAL JUDGE THAT
GAVE HIM A LENIENT SENTENCE LATE
LASTEEK FOR SEPARATE CRIMES.
ALSO, AT ANY MOMENT, RER
STONE'S FORMER LAWYERS WILL
FORMALLY SUBMIT THEIR ARGUMENT
TO HER, TO JUDGE JACKSON,
BASICALLY TRYING TO CONVINCE HER
THAT ROGER STONE DIDN'T REALLY
VIOLATE HER GAG ORDER.
HE IS SOMETHING OF AN INSTAGRAM
BAND DID, AS YOU MAY KNOW, AND
HE HAD THE RECENT POSTS WHICH
APPEARED TO VIOLATE THE GAG
ORDER.
SHE COULD JAIL HIM FOR THAT,
ALSO THIS WEEK.
AS SOON AS THAT FILING COMES IN,
I CAN TELL YOU WE'LL REPORT IT
OUT FOR YOU.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHAT IT MEANS.
THERE ARE ALSO DEVELOPMENTS
KICKING UP IN THE MUELLER PROBE
THIS WEEK.
WEDNESDAY MANAFORT RECVE THAT
SENTENCE IN THE D.C. CASE THAT
COULD BE UP TO TEN SEPARATE
YEARS IN PRISON.
THEN YOU HAVE MUELLER AND
MICHAEL FLYNN'S LAWYERS
PROVIDING AN UPDATE THAT COULD
DETERMINE WHETHER THOSE PEOPLE
ARE READY FOR SENTENCING.
THEN COMES THE STONE DAY
THURSDAY WITH JUDGE JACKSON.
IDAY TN WE'LL ALSO GET AN
UPDATE OVER WHETHER MANAFORT'S
DEPUTY RICK GATES CAN BE
SENTENCED OR WHETHER MUELLER
NEEDS MORE TIME WITH HIM AS
WELL.
SO THAT'S A LOT OF ACTION RIGHT
INSIDE THE COURTROOM.
THEN OUTSIDE OF IT, YOU HAVE
PRESIDENT TRUMP REPORTEDLY
PRIVATY HAILING MANAFORT FOR
NOT BEING A RAT OR A COWARD AND
LIKENING HIM TO A, QUOTE,
POLITICAL PRISONER.
ON ALL OF THE LEGALITIES, I WANT
TO BEGIN WITH TWO FORMER FEDERAL
PROSECUTORS, GLEN KIRSHNER AND
PAUL HENDERSON.
GOOD EVENING, JEFF.
>> GOOD EVENING.
THANKS FOR HAVING US.
>> GLEN, WHAT DO YOU SEE IS
IMPORTANT IN THIS BIG WEEK?
>> YOU KNOW, I'M ACTUALLY
LOOKING FORWARD TO THE MANAFORT
SENTENCING, BECAUSE I THINK
JUDGE ELLIS IS REALLY UNJUST AND
UNJUSTIFIABLE SENTENCE OF
MAFO SO FAR BELOW THE
GUIDELINES WITH REALLY NO
JUSTIFICATION FOR IT.
DOES HARM NOT ONLY TO SORT OF
THE MUELLER PROBE, BUT REALLY TO
OUR CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM.
YOU KNOW, THERE ARE A COUPLE OF
REASONS WHY A JUDGE CAN DEPART
DOWNWARD, THAT IS GO BELOW WHAT
IS SUPPOSED TO BE THE BOTTOM OF
THE POTENTIAL SENTENCE FOR
MANAFORT OF 19 1/2 YEARS.
AND THE JUDGE ACTUALLY ANNOUNCED
THAT NEITHER OF THOSE THINGS
APPLIED.
HE DIDN'T ACCEPT RESPONSIBILITY
FOR HIS CRIMES AND HE DIDN'T
SUBSTANTIALLY ASSIST THE
GOVERNMENT IN OTHER
INVESTIGATIONS.
FACT, WE KNOW JUDGE JACKSON
FOUND HE LIED TO THE MUELLER
PRECUTORS ON, AMONG OTHER
THINGS, ONE OF THE CENTRAL
ISSUES TO THE MUELLER PROBE.
SO FOR THEM TO HAVE JUDGE ELLIS
ANNOUNCE THAT HE'S GOING FROM
19 1/2 DOWN TO JUST 3 YEARS AND
LEONARDO MONTHS I THINK REALLY
DOES DAMAGE IN SO MANY WAYS TO
THE SYSTEM.
I THINK JUDGE JACKSON, WHO IS
STRONG, INDEPENDENT, SMART, NO
NONSENSE AND LAW AND ORDER IS
GOING TO GET THE MANAFORT
SENTENCE RIGHT.
AND FOR THIS FORMER CAREER
PROSECUTOR, THOSE THINGS STILL
ER.
>> SO, PAUL, I WONDER IF YOU
COULD HANDICAP BOTH OF THESE BIG
RULINGS THIS WEEK.
SHE IS IN THE CENTER OF IT.
AND ROGER STONE'S ARGUMENTS,
WHICH WE'RE GOING REPORT IN
DETAIL AS SOON AS WE GET THEM,
THEY MAY BE A VY SIMPLE
VERSION OF OUTKAST, I'M SORRY
MISS JACKSON, ADMIT
RESPONSIBILITY AND HOPE YOU
DON'T GET JAILED.
WHAT DOES MANAFORT SEE HAPPENING
IN BOTH OF THE PROCEEDINGS?
>> I THINK THE HAMMER IS GOING
TO FALL AND IT'S GOING FALL VERY
SEVERELY ON JACKSON.
AND ALL OF THE OTHER REPORTS ARE
ONLY GOING TO MAKE THAT SENTENCE
EVEN WORSE FOR HIM.
I THINK THE REAL ISSUE HERE, AND
WHAT A LOT OF FOLKS HAVE BEEN
TALKING ABOUT IS WHETHER OR NOT
THESE SENTENCES ARE GOING TO BE
CONCURRENT OR CONSECUTIVE.
AND HERE THESE ARE SEPARATE
CRIMES.
I THINK IT'S CLEAR THAT THIS
JUDGE IS MOVING IN THE DIRECTION
THAT THE SENTENCES ARE NOT GOING
TO BE CONCURRENT.
>> YOU'RE TALKING WITH MANAFORT
WHETHER SHE TAKES THE FOUR THAT
HE'S GOT IN THIS OTHER LENIENT
CASE AND ADDS TO THAT RATHER
THAN COMBINING?
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT IT MEANS.
IS SHE GOING TO LET THEM RUN
SIMPLY OR GOING TO RUN
CONCURRENTLY.
I THINK SHE IS GOING TO LET THEM
SEPARATELY BECAUSE OF ALL OF THE
DISPARITIES WE'VE SEEN THIS CASE
AND THE HUGE DISPARITY WE'VE
SEEN IN THE FIRST CASE WITH
ELLIS.
THIS IS BEFORE WE EVEN START
TALKING ABOUT THE HUGE ECONOMIC
AND RACE DISPARITIES THAT WE SEE
IN FEDERAL SENTENCING.
BUT IN THIS CASE IN PARTICULAR
THAT IS SO FAR BELOW THE
STANDARD AND THE GUIDELINE THAT
WE'VE SEEN, I THINK JACKSON
AFTER THIS 17 MONTHS OF DEALING
WITH THIS CASE AND THE 500
MOTIONS THAT HAVE BEEN FILED
BACK AND FORTH, IN ADDITION TO
BREAKING HIS PLEA DEAL AND THE
BAD BEHAVIOR BOTH FROM MANAFORT
AND HIS REPRESENTATIVES, NOW IS
THE TIME TO ADDRESS ALL OF THOSE
TRANSGRESSIONS IN SENTENCING.
ALL OF THOSE ARE AGGRAVATING
FACTORS.
>> DO YOU EXPECT JUDGE JACKSON
HAT
HAPPENED ELSEWHERE OR IS SHE
GOING TO STAY LASER FOCUSED ON
THESE CHARGES?
>> I THINK SHE IS GOING TO STAY
LASER FOCUSED IN THESE CHARGES,
BUT SHE HAS TO TAKE IO ACCOUNT
AND CONTEMPLATE SOME OF THE
BIGGER PICTURE IN TERMS OF
WHAT'S HAPPENING WITH THE
MUELLER PROBE AND WHAT'S
HAPPENING WITH HIS
CO-CONSPIRATORS BECAUSE THAT'S
ONE OF THE CHARGES THAT HE'S
PLEAD TO IS HERE THE OBSTRUCTION
OF JUSTICE AND ALSO THE
CONSPIRACY AGAINST THE UNITED
STATES.
EACH OF THOSE CHARGES HE'S GOT
TEN YEARS EACH FOR THOSE
CHARGES.
SO EVEN IF SHE BLENDS THEM
TOGETHER AND JUST GIVES HIM THE
TEN Y WHEN HE IS FACING
ACTUALLY TWO DECADES, I THINK HE
IS LIKELY TO LOOK AT A SENTENCE
OF SOMETHING LIKE 14 YEARS.
BUT EVEN IF ROLLS THEM IN
AND CONTEMPLATES THE MITIGATING
FACTORS WHICH I DON'T THINK SHE
IS LIKELY TO DO BECAUSE OF HIS
BEHAVIOR IN THIS CASE, I STILL
THINK IT'S GOING TO BE AROUND 14
YEARS AND NOT THE 10 OR
SOMETHING LOWER.
>> AND, GLENN, ONE OF THE
REASONS THAT THE COUNTRY HAS
BEEN HAVING A BIG DEBATE OVER
CRIMINAL JUSTICE INEQUITY SINCE
THURSDAY NIGHT IS A GOOD THING
THAT EXPOSES AAD THING.
THE BAD THING ACCORDING TO MANY
PEOPLE IS THE VERY CELEBRATE
IMPORTANT INEQUITIES THAT WERE
REVEALED IN JUDGE ELLIS'
APPROACH.
THE GOOD THING IS THAT WE DO
HAVE TRANSPARENT FEDERAL COURTS
WHICH MEANS IN OUR DEMOCRACY, IN
OUR RULEF LAW, THE CITIZENRY
LEARNS IN REALTIME NOT ONLY THE
RESULT, BUT JUDGES HAVE TO SIT
THERE AND EXPLAIN THEMSELVES,
AND THAT THAT CAN HAVE A
POSITIVE FACTOR HERE THAT CAN BE
PART OF THE PROCESS OF
ACCOTABILI.
I MENTION THAT LOOKING FORWARD
TO JUDGE JACKSON BECAUSE
ALTHOUGH SHE HAS NOT BEEN
CRITICIZED THE WAY JUDGE ELLIS
HAS, THAT SAME TRANSPARENCY PUT
HER ON RECORD AS SAYING NO MORE
DO-OVERS FOR MR. STONE.
AND WE ALL KNOW THA NOW.
I WONDER HOW YOU THINK THAT
FACTORS IN.
I'M GOING READ YOU FROM WHAT SHE
TOLD ROGER STONE THE LAST TIME
OVER THE GAG ORDER.
I GAVE YOU A SECOND CHANCE.
THIS ISN'T BASEBALL.
YOU DON'T GET A THIRD CHANCE.
OU THINK HER SAYING THAT ON
THE RECORD AND THE NATION
KNOWING IT REALLY RAISES THE
PRESSURE ON HER TO HAVE
MEANINGFUL PUNISHMENT FOR HIM
NOW?
>> THAT'S A GREAT QUESTION, ARI,
CAUSE SHE DID PUT HERSELF SORT
OF IN A BIT OF A BOX BY SAYING
YOU DON'T GET A THIRD CHANCE.
BUT LET ME TELL YOU, I THINK SHE
IS GOING TO SEE STONE'S
TRANSGRESSION HERE AS A BIT OF A
FOUL TIP.
I HAVE A FNG SHE IS NOT YET
READY TO, AS WE SAY IN D.C.,
STEP 'EM BACK, WHICH IS
BASICALLY TAKE HIM INTO CUSTODY
AND DETAIN HIM PENDING TRIAL.
WE SAW THE POST W HE SAID
WHO FRAMED ROGER STONE, WHICH
DOES SEEM TO VIOLATE THE
MODIFIED GAG ORDER THAT SHE
HANDED DOWN LAST TIME.
WE DID H THAT I GUESS A
RERELEASE OF A BOOK IS IN
PROGRESS.
I JUST DON'T KNOW THAT SHE'S
GOING TO SEE THIS AS ENOUGH OF A
DIRECT TRANSGRESSION OF HER
MODIFIED GAG ORDER.
>> SO LET ME ASK YOU.
ISN'T THIS THE ISSUE WITH ROGER
IS THAT HE PARSES AND PETTY FOGS
HIS WA TO T BOUNDARY?
I THINK YOU GUYS HAVE BOTH DEALT
WITH CASES WHERE PEOPLE HAVE
DONE LESS AND ALREADY BEEN HIT
WITH MORE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> AND HE DOES IT FOR THE
ATTENTION.
I THINK HE IS GETTING EXACTLY
WHAT HE WANTS.
BUT I HAVE A FEELING SHE IS
GOING TO TREAT HIM LIKE THE
TEENAGER THAT 'S BEHAVING
LIKE.
SHE IS GOING TO TAKE HIS PHONE.
SHE IS GOING TO BAN HIM FROM
SOCIAL MEDIA.
SHE IS GOING TO SEND HIM TO HIS
ROOM, PERHAPS PUT HIM ON HOME
DETENTION WITH ELECTRONIC
MONITORING VIA A GPS ANKLE
BRACELET, AND I THINK SHE IS
GOING TO CALL THIS ONE A FOUL
ND GIVE HIM ONE MORE
CHANCE, AND THEN IF HE VIOLATES,
STEP HIM BACK.
I COULD BE WRONG.
SHE NO NONSENSE.
SHAY SAY YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'VE ALREADY HAD ENOUGH WITH
YOU.
>> STAY WITH THE ME.
I'M GOING TO BRING IN TO OUR
CONVERSATION SHELBY HOL WHO
IS NOT A REPORTER BUT SURE
SPENDS A LOT OF TIME WITH
REPORTERS ON THE STORY.
>> WHICH IS FUN.
I ENJOY IT.
>> IF YOU WANT TO BE TOUGH ON
MR. STONE, HE'S CLEARLY GONE UP
TO THE LINE OVER AND OVER.
IF YOU WANT TO BE BENIGN ABOUT
IT, YOU SAY HE DIDN'T GO GIVE A
SPEECH OR DO SOMETHING WE WOULD
CALL THE TRADITIONAL VIOLATION.
HE KEEPS USING INSTA STORIES AS
A WAY TO TIPTOE AROUND AND MESS
WITH IT.
>> HE LIKES TO PLAY WITH FIRE.
WHEN YOU TALK TOEGAL EXPERTS,
YOU SAY THIS MAY NOT BE
BLATANTLY OVER THE LINE BUT HE
SURE AS HECK IS WALKING VERY
CLOSE TO IT.
THAT'S HIS PERSONALITY.
I THINK WHAT'S TO INTERESTING
ABOUT THIS WEEK IS JUDGE JACKSON
WILL SENTENCE PAUL MANAFORT AND
SEND A SIGNAL TO ROGER STONE.
THAT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE HER
INTENTION, BUT WHATEVER COMES OF
THAT SENTENCING WILL BE WATCHED
VERY CLOSELY BY ROGER STONE
BECAUSE HE'S COMING UP TO THE
PELINE NEXT.
I THINK WITH THE FOUR YEARS THAT
MANAFO GOT LAST WEEK, A LOT OF
PEOPLE WERE FRUSTRATED.
A LOT OF MUELLER WATCHERS AND
LEGAL EXPERTS WERE FRUSTRATED
THAT THAT SENDS A SIGNAL TO
OTHERS WRAPPED UP IN THE
3450U8ER PROBE THAT MAYBE YOU
DON'T HAVE TO COOPERATE.
MAYBE YOU CAN LIE THE
PROSECUTORS.
MAYBE YOU CAN BREAK THE TERMS OF
YOUR BAIL, DO ALL OF THESE BAD
THINGS AND STILL KIND OF GET OFF
THE HOOK.
NOW FOUR YEARS IS NOT NOTHING.
THAT IS A SIGNIFICANT JAIL
SENTENCE.
>> RIGHT.
>> WHAT HE WAS FACING --
>> IT'S A SLICE.
IT'S A TINY SLICE BASED ON WHAT
HE DID AND WHAT HE WAS UP FOR.
>> RIGHT.
AND THEN YOU HAVE ALL OF THIS
RUMOR MONGERING ABOUT WHETHER
HIS LAWYER EMPHASIZING NO
COLLUSION OTHER THAN LEGAL
DENIALS IS AN APPEAL FOR A
PARDON.
HERE IS THE WHITE HOUSE
RESPONDING AGAIN TO ALL OF THESE
RUMORS TODAY.
>> PAUL MANAFORT GOES FOR THE
SECOND HALF OF HIS SENTENCING
THIS WEEK.
WHY HAVEN'T THE PRESIDENT RULED
OUT A PARDON FOR PAUL MANAFORT?
>>HE PRESIDENT HAS MADE HIS
POSITION ON THAT CLEAR, AND
HE'LL MAKE A DECISION WHEN HE IS
READY.
>> THIS IS A FASCINATING -- THAT
WAS A FASCINAING POINT THAT
SARAH HUCKABEE SANDERS MADE,
BECAUSE EVEN PROSECUTORS NOTE
THEY'D THOUG PAUL MANAFORT
MIGHT BE ANGLING FOR A PARDON
AND THEREFORE REFUSING TO
COOPERATE FULLY.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN VERY
NONCOMMITTAL ON THIS ISSUE,
WHICH MAKES A LOT OF PEOPLE
THINK HE WILL ISSUE A PARDON,
AND SOME OF PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
SUPPORTERS WANT TO ISSUE A
PARDON, BUT I JUST THINK YOU
HAVE TO STEP BACK AND LOOK AT
THE HUGE RANGE OF CRIMES PAUL
MANAFORT HAS EITHER PLEADED
GUILTY TO OR BEEN CONVICTED OF,
AND YOU ALSO HAVE TO LOOK AT AN
AMERICA FIRST PRESIDENT COULD
POTENTIALLY PARDON SOMEONE WHO
CONSPIRED AGAINST THE UNITED
STATES AND HAS YET TO EVEN
APOLOGIZE TO AMERICANS FOR THAT.
I THINK THAT'S A BIG POLITICAL
CALCULATION IF THE PRESIDENT'S
REALLY THINKING ABOUT A PARDON,
WHETHER OR NOT IT'S WORTH IT,
WHETHER OR NOT IT'S WORTH
SPENDING THAT POLITICAL CAPAL
REMAINS TO BE SEEN.
>> GLENN, ON THAT POINT?
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW, THIS IS MAN
WHO STOLE FROM THE UNITED STATES
BY FAILING TO PAY HIS TAXES,
ENGAGED IN BANK FRAUD, ENGAGED
IN CONSPIRACY AGAINST THE UNITED
STATES BY ILLEGALLY LOBBYING,
AND HE COMMITTED WITNESS
TAMPERING.
HERI TO URGE WITNESSES TO
LIE SO HE IS DISRESPECTFUL OF
THE COUNTRY.
HE IS DISRESPECTFUL OF THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE, HANDY IS
DISRESPECTFUL OF THE CRIMINAL
JUSTICE SYSTEM.
FOR THE PRESIDENT TO COME OUT
AND SAY HE IS NOT A RAT, HE IS
NOT A COWARD, HE IS A BRAVE MAN,
THAT'S THE EXACT OPPOSITE OF THE
MESSAGE THAT A LAW-ABIDING
PRESIDENT WOULD BE SENDING.
>> AND PAUL, TAKE A LISTEN TO
HOW PAUL MANAFORT SPOKE ABOUT
ALL OF THIS BACK IN THE BETTER
DAYS WHEN HE AND ROGER WERE
TOASTING EACH OTHER FOR THEIR
PROXIMITY TO DONALD TRUMP.
>> ROGER RECOMMEND YOU FOR THE
JOB?
>> ROGER WAS ONE OF THE TWO OR
THREE PEOPLE WHO STRONGLY
RECOMMENDED ME, YES.
EVEN AFTER ROGER STOPPED BEING
THE PRINCIPLE POLITICAL ADVISER
TO PRESIDENT TRUMP, HE CONTINUED
TO BE AN IMPORTANT POLITICAL
ADVISER AND IS TO THIS DAY.
>> TAKE IT ALL TOGETHER FOR US,
PAUL.
YOU SEE THESE INDIVIDUALS, ONE A
CONVICTED FELON WAITING FOR A
POTENTIAL SENTENCE OF UP TO TEN
MORE YEARS.
THE OTHER LITERALLY PLEADING FOR
HIS LIBERTY BEFORE HE GOES TO
TRIAL.
HOW DOES THIS COMPARE TO OTHER
LEGAL CASES YOU'VE BEEN INVOLVED
IN WHEN YOU SEE PEOPLE FLYING SO
HIGH,OW EVEN ON A BEST CASE
SCENARIO, EVEN THE QUOTE/UNQUOTE
LENIENT SENTENCE FACING REAL
TOUGH TIMES?
>> I THINK THAT LENIENCY IS OUT
THE WINDOW.
AND WHEN YOU H THESE PLEASE
THAT THEY'RE MAKING NOW TO STAY
OUT OF CUSTODY, I THINK IT'S
GOING TO FALL ON DEAF EARS.
I THINK THOSE STATEMENTS THAT WE
HEARD ARE ALL GOING TO COME BACK
AND BITE THEM.
THEY'RE ALL GOING TO BE USED AS
STATEMENTS IN AGGRAVATION WHEN
THEY'RE CONTINUE PL ALL O
THE SENTENCES.
I CAN ALREADY ANTICIPATE THE
ARGUMENTS THAT PROSECUTORS ARE
GOING TO BEAKING JUST TO GET
THE SENTENCE, AND I BELIEVE THAT
THIS SENTENCE IS GOING TO BE
MUCH MORE HARSH THAN THE FIRST
SENTENCEH ELLIS, AND I THINK
WE'RE GOING TO SEE SOME SERIOUS
TIME, AND IT'S NOT GOING TO
MATTER THAT THIS HAS BEEN A
HIGH-FLYING POLITICAL INSIDER.
WHAT'S GOING TO MATTER IS HIS
BEHAVIOR THROUGHOUT THIS TRIAL,
HIS BEHAVIOR WITH THE PLEA
BARGAINING, HIS BEHAVIOR WITH
THE ASSOCIATION WITH ALL OF
THESE OTHER FOLKS AROUND HIM
THAT HAVE ENGAGED IN ALL OF THIS
TERRIB HAVIOR.
ALL OF THAT ADDS TO MORE YEARS.
ALL OF THAT ADDS TO A NOT
CONSIDERING A MITIGATING FACTOR
TO KEEP SOMEONE OR RUN A
SENTENCE THAT'S GOING TO BE
CONCURRENT.
WHAT'S GOING TO RESULT HERE IS A
HEAVY STACK OF SENTENCES AND A
HEAVY STACK OF YEARS I BELIEVE
FOR MANAFORT.
AND WE'RE GOING SEE THAT IN A
MATTER OF DAYS.
MY GUESS IS 14 YEARS OR MORE FOR
THESE CHARGES.
AND YOU -- MAYBE WE WILL SEE A
CHANGE IN ATTITUDE.
I WILL SAY THAT I THINK THAT'S
REALLY IMPORTANT THAT WE HAVE
NOT HEARD AN APOLOGY.
WE HAVE NOT HEARD MANAFORT COME
FORWARD AND SAY THAT HE IS
SORRY, THAT HE REGTS HIS
CRIMES THAT HE'S COMMITTED, HIS
CRIMES THAT HE HAS PLEAD TO.
ALL OF THAT I THINK PUTS THE
JUDGE IN A SITUATION WHERE SHE'S
GOING TO SHOW HIM.
>> RIGHT.
>> THAT SHE IS IN CHARGE.
>> SHE HAS NOT APPRECIATED HIS
BEHAVIOR.
>> RIGHT.
>> HE HAS PLAYED GAIMT GAMES
WITH HER.
SO THAT'S WHAT IS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
>> PAUL HENDERSON, GLENN
KIRSHNER AND SHELBY HOLIDAY,
THANK YOU.
COMING UP, LAYING DOWN A NEW
MARKER ON HOW AND WHEN THE HOUSE
WOULD EVER IMPEACH DONALD TRUMP.
LIVE ON THAT BIG STORY LATER.
>>> AND LATER FROM THE HUSH
MONEY SCANDAL, BREAKING HIS
SILENCE TALKING ABO COHEN AND
THE MOTIVATION, THE "ACCESS
HOLLYWOOD" TAPE.
>>> PLUS, SOME BIG NEWS FROM THE
2020 PRESIDENTIAL RACE AFTER OUR
ROCK INTERVIEW RIGHT HERE
WITH SENATOR ELIZABETH WARREN.
MORE ON THE FOURTH OF JULY AND
FOLLOW-UP FROM THAT.
>>> AND THEN ONE OF THE MOST
CREATIVE MINDS BEHIND CURB AND
SIGN FIELD.
ALL OF THAT AND MORE.
YOU'RE WATCHING "THE BEAT" ON
NBC.
This is your invitation to a
higher standard of luxury.
This ithe invitation
to Lexus sales event.
Lease the 2019 ES 350 for
$379 a month for 36 months.
Now thru March 31st.
Experience amazing
at your Lexus dealer.
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it from
your allergy pills?
Most pills don't    finb
because they don't relieve
nasal congestion.
Flonase Sensimist
is different.
It relieves all
your worst symptoms,
including nasal ngti,
which most pills don't.
It's more complete
allergy relief.
And all from a gentle mist
you can barely feel.
Flonase Sensimist helps block
six key inflammatory
substances.
you can barely feel.
Most pills only block one.
And six is
greater than one.
Flonase Sensimist.
Staying at Hampton
for a work trip.
When your
flight gets in late,
it's never too
early for coffee.
Oh no no no.
Your new boss
seems cool,
but she might not
be sweatpants cool.
Who is THAT
ready THIS early?
It's only 7 am.
Somebody help me.
Close call.
Not quite ready
to face the day?
That's why we're here
with free hot breakfast
and a warm welcome.
Book at Hampton.com for
our Price Match Guarantee.
Hampton by Hilton.
I wanna keep doing what I love,
that's the retirement plan.
Book at Hampton.com for
our Price Match Guarantee.
With my annuity,
I know there is a guarantee.
It's for my family,
its for my self,
its for my future.
Annuities can provide
protected income for life.
Learn more at
Retire Your Risk dot org.
My name is Austin,
I am a two-time
brain cancer conqueror.
There are some days
when I have my, my downs
and then I have to rely on
my mom to come
pick me up from work.
We need to be connected
on a regular basis.
Sometimes I get
hundreds of texts from her
and I'm like stop.
I owe everything to her,
she's my world.
I love you mom.
I love you too.
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now comes with
Apple Music on us.
Get a free Galaxy S10e
when youuy the new Galaxy S10.
>>> BREAKING NEWS TONIGHT.
SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI IS
DECLARING SOMETHING OF A NEW
STANDARD ON THE RECORD FOR WHAT
IT WOULD TAKE TO IMPEACH
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
IN A BRAND-NEW INTERVIEW WITH
"THE WASHINGTON POST" MAGAZINE,
SPEAKER PELOSI SAYS THAT IT'S
JUST NOT WORTH IT TO PURSUE
IMPEACHMENT AT THIS TIME AND
SAYS IN ORDER TO PURSUE IT, SHE
WOULD NEED COMPELLING EVIDENCE
AND A BIPARTISAN PROCESS.
SHE ALSO PREFACED HER REMARKS BY
SAYING THIS IS NEWS, SUGGESTING
FOR WHATEVER REASON WANTS TO PUT
A MARKER DOWN TONIGHT.
AND HERE IS ONE OTHER REASON
WHY.
POLITICALLY, AS YOU MAY HAVE
HEARD, THERE ARE GROWING CALLS
FROM HER OWN CAUCUS, FROM HER
OWN DEMOCRATIC MEMBER SAYING
MAYBE IT IS TIME TO CONSIDER
IMPEACHMENT.
>> I RISE TODAY, MR. SPEAKER, TO
CALL FOR THE IMPEACHMENT OF THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
OF AMERICA.
>> I BELIEVE THAT WE HAVE
EVERYTHING THAT IT NEEDS TO
BASICALLY IMPEACH HIM.
>> YEAH.
>> I BELIEVE THAT.
>> BULLIES DON'T N, AND I SAID
BABY, THEY DON'T.
BECAUSE WE'RE GOING GO IN THERE
AND WE'RE GOING IMPEACH THE
[ BLEEP ].
>> I'M NOW JOINED BY MEMBER OF
SPEAKER PELOSI'S LEADERSHIP TEAM
FROM THE HOUSE DEMOCRATIC
CAUCUS, AS WELL AS A MEMBER OF
THE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE,
RELEVANT FOR ALL THESE REASONS.
CONGRESSMAN HAKEEM JEFFRIES,
THANKS FOR JOINING ME TONIGHT.
>> GOOD TO BE WITH YOU, ARI.
>> THE BOTTOM LINE, THE SPEAKER
TRYING TO MAKE NEWS HERE AND
RAISE THE BAR AND THUS THE
EXPECTATIONS ON WHAT IT WOULD
TAKE TO IMPEACH PRESIDENT TRUMP?
>> I THINK WHAT THE SPEAKER IS
DOING IS DRAWING A CLEAR
DELINEATION IN TMSF WHAT THE
HOUSE DEMOCRATIC CAUCUS IS ALL
ABOUT.
WE DIDN'T RUN A CAMPAIGN LAST
YEAR AND SEIZE CONTROL OF THE
HOUSE OF REPSENTATIVES BASED
ON A DESIRE TO IMPEACH THE
PRESIDENT.
WE RAN A CAMPAIGN ON THE FOR THE
PEOPLE AGENDA INDICATING WE WERE
GOING TO FOCUS ON DRIVE DO YOU
THINK THE HIGH COSTS OF
LIFE-SAVING PRESCRIPTION DRUGS,
INCREASE PAY FOR EVERY DAY
AMERICAS, ENACT A INFRASTRUCTURE
PLAN AND CLEAN UP CORRUPTION AND
BRING OUR DEMOCRACY TO LIFE
THAT'S WHAT WE RAN ON.
THAT'S WHAT THE SPEAKER
APPROPRIATELY WANTS TO KEEP OUR
FOCUS ON AS WE MOVE FORWARD.
>> THAT MAKES SENSE.
I'M GOING PUSH YOU ON IT,
THOUGH.
I THINK EVERYTHING YOU SAID IS
ABOUT SUPPORTING BASICALLY THE
POLICY AGENDA TO TRY TO IMPROVE
WORKING PEOPLE'S LIVES ACROSS
AMERICA.
NO DOUBT THERE IS A RECORD ON
THAT.
BUT WOULDN'T YOU AGREE WITH ME,
REAL TALK, THAT THE MAJORITY OF
PEOP I YOUR DISTRICT, THE
MAJORITY OF DEMOCRATIC VOTERS
ALREADY THINK THAT DONALD TRUMP
HAS ABUSED HIS POWER, AND THEY
WERE EXPECTING, AT LEAST WAITING
UNTIL MUELLER ISSUES HIS
FINDINGS TO SAY WHETHER OR NOT
THERE WOULD BE POTENTIAL
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS?
>> THAT'S CORRECT.
I DON'T THINK ANYTHING THE
SPEAKER SAID IS INCONSISTENT
WITH THAT NOTION THAT WE'RE
GOING TO TAKE A WAIT AND SEE
APPROACH AS IT RELATES TO THE
INVESTIGATION BEING CONDUCTED BY
BOB MUELLER, AS WELL AS THE
THE SOUTHERN DISTRICT OF NEW
YORK.
AT THE END OF THE DAY,
IMPEACHMENT IS THE ULTIMATE
POLITICAL DEATH PENALTY.
IT INCLUDED IN THE CONSTITUTION
FOR EXTRAORDINARY CIRCUMSTANCES.
AS THE SPEAKER POINTED OUT, WE
SHOULD ONLY PROCEED ABSENT A
COMPELLING FINDING THAT ALLOWS
US TO MAKE AN ABSOLE
DETERMINATION TO GO DOWN THIS
ROAD.
>> CONGRESSMAN, SHE DIDN'T JUST
REFER TO THE EVIDENCE WHICH IS
WHAT YOU'RE CALLING WAIT AND
SEE.
SHE SAID AS PART OF THE STANDARD
THIS WOULD HAVE TO BE,
QUOTE/UNQUOTE, BIPARTISAN.
AND YOU KNOW A LOT OF PEOPLE
LOOK AT THE CONDUCT OF THE
REPUBLICANS IN THE TRUMP ERA,
AND THEY SAY WHY WOULD ANYONE
WITH SUBPOENA POWER RUNNING THE
HOUSE WAIT ON THEM TO MAK THEIR
OWN INDEPENDENT JUDGMENT ABOUT
WHAT MUELLER MAY OR MAY NOT
FIND?
>> WELL TWO, THINGS.
WE'RE GOING CONTINUE OUR
AGGRESSIVE OVERSIGHT FUNCTION AS
IT RELATES TO BEING A CHECK AND
BALANCE ON AN OUT-OF-CONTROL
UTIVERANCH THAT IS OUR
RESPONSIBILITY.
WITH RESPECT TO IMPEACHMENT, AS
YOU KNOW, LISTEN, THE HOUSE
FUNDAMENTALLY IS THE GRAND JURY.
THE SENATE IS THE ULTIMATE JURY.
>> UH-HUH.
>> IMPEACHMENT IS LIKE AN
INDICTMENT, AND WE CAN INDICT IN
THE HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES IF
THE EVIDENCE IS COMPELLING
ENOUGH TO MOVE FORWARD.
BUT THE ULTIMATE OBJECTIVE
PRESUMABLY OF THE PEOPLE WHO
BELIEVE APPROPRIATELY THAT
DONALD TRUMP HAS PRESIDED OVER
CHAOS, CRISIS, CONFUSION, AND A
CULTURE OF CORRUPTION IS TO
REMOVE HIM.
AND WHAT THE SPEAKER HAS MADE
CLEAR IS TO GET TO REMOVAL, YOU
WILL ND AT LEAST 20 REPUBLICAN
SENATORS IN THE OTHER HOUSE OF
CONGRESS.
THAT'S REALITY.
>> YOU'RE SPEAKING TO AN
INTRICACY THAT YOU MAY KNOW OF
BECAUSE YOU DEAL WITH HER DAILY
THAT WASN'T QUITE IN HER
STATEMENT, WHICH IS MAKING WAVES
TONIGHT.
ARE YOU SAYING THAT SHE'S
BASICALLY LAYING OUT A POSITION
THAT SHE'S NOT GOING TO GO NEWT
AND GO IN WITH A BATTLE PLAN
THAT IS ON AARTISAN BASIS IN
THE HOUSE WITHOUT A LONGER TERM
STRATEGY OF WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE
IN THE SENATE, AND YOU WOULD
HAVE THE BUILD EITHER THROUGH
THE EVENTS, THE EVIDENCE
WHATEVER IS UNCOVERED ABOUT THE
PRESIDENT, YOU HAVE TO BUILD THE
SUPPORT FOR THAT BEING A
POSSIBILITY IN THE SENATE,
OTHERWISE IT'S NOT WORTH IT TO
GETT STARTED AT ALL?
>> WELL, I HAVEN'T HAD AN
OPPORTUNITY TO SPEAK THAT
DIRECTLY WITH SPEAKER PELOSI
ABOUT THE CONTEXT OF THOSE
REMARKS BUT I CAN INTERPRET
THEM.
>> I'VE HEARD YOU GUYS ARE
TIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT I HEARD.
I HEARD YOU GUYS TALKING ABOUT
THEM.
>> WE'RE ALL DOWN WITH NDP.
BUT ATTEND OF THE DAY, I DO KNOW
THAT CHAIRMAN JERRY NADLER,
SPEAKER PELOSI ON OTHER
OCCASIONS, MYSELF AND OTHER
MEMBERS OF THE HOUSE DEMOCRATIC
LEADERSHIP HAVE MADE THE
OBSERVATION THAT THERE IS A
DISTINCTION BETWEEN IMPEACHMENT
AND REMOVAL, AND THAT IN ORDER
FOR US TO PROCEED, ULTIMATELY,
IF THERE IS A CONCLUSION THAT
THIS PRESIDENT HAS PRESIDED OVER
A CULTF CRIMINALITY AND
CORRUPTION IS TOTALLY OUT OF
CONTROL SO THAT THE ULTIMATE
POLITICAL DEATH PENALTY IS
MERITED, YOU HAVE TO DO IT IN A
BIPARTISAN WAY IF YOU'RE GOING
GET TO REMOVAL.
WE CAN INDICT IN THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES, BUT IN ORDER TO
CONVICT, IT HAS TO BE DONE WITH
DEMOCRATS AND REPUBLICANS AND
THE FULL SUPPORT OF THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE.
I AGREE WITH SPEAKER PELOSI THAT
THAT IS THE REASONABLE WAY TO
PROCEED.
>> VERY INTERESTING, BECAUSE
THIS IS MAKING WAVES, AND SHE'S
OBVIOUSLY SPEAKING TO A
CONSTITUENCY THAT'S GOT WHOLE
BUNCH OF DIFFERENT VIEWS ON,
AGAIN, ON WHAT YOU CALL THE
DOCUNTED CORRUPTION OF THIS
PARTICULAR PRESIDENT.
CONGRESSMAN HAKEEM JEFFRIES FROM
LEADERSHIP, THANKS FOR JOINING
ME TONIGHT.
>> THANK YOU, ARI.
>> APPRECIATE IT, SIR.
>>> UP AHEAD, AOC MAKING WAVES
OF HER OWN AT THE SOUTH BY
SOUTHWEST CONFERENCE TALKING
ABOUT LIBERALS AND MODERATES.
>>> BUT FIRST, THE LAWYER WHO
STUCK ON STORMY DANIELS' HUSH
MONEY DEAL, WHO WAS ALL INVOLVED
IN IT, WHO WASN'T SPEAKING,
WELL, HE IS BREAKING HIS
SILENCE.
WE HAVE MORE ON THAT WHEN WE
BACK IN 30.
WE
BACK IN 30
♪ Do you love me? ♪
♪ I'm in the groove ♪
♪ Now do you love me? ♪
♪ Do you love me
now that I can dance? ♪
Applebee's
3 Course Meal.
Now that's
Eatin' Good
in the Neighborhood.
Fidelity is redefining value.
Introducg roccount fees
for brokerage accounts.
And zero minimums
to open an account.
At Fidelity,
those zeros really add up.
♪ Maybe I'll win,
saved by zero ♪
>>> HERE IS THE HEADLINE.
IT WAS POLITICAL.
THAT IS WHAT THE FOR LAWYER
FOR STORMY DANIELS AND KAREN
McDOUGLE IS SAYING ABOUT THESE
HUSH MONEY PAYMENTS THAT HE
ORIGINALLY NEGOTIATED.
YOU MAY REMEMBER THE NAME.
KEITH DAVIDSON WAS THE LAWYER
BEFORE MIKE MICHAEL AVENATTI, A
SAYS IT WAS THE RELEASE OF THE
NEW INFAMOUS "ACCESS HOLLYWOOD"
TAPE THAT CHANGED EVERYTHING.
>> THE "ACCESS HOLLYWOOD" TAPE
WAS THE MOTIVATING FACTOR IN
THIS CASE ACTUALLY RESOLVING.
IT DEFEATS THE ARGUMENT THAT
THIS WAS DONE FOR PURELY
PERSONAL REASON AND THAT THIS
WAS IN FACT DONE FOR POLITICAL
REASONS BECAUSE AFTER THE
"ACCESS HOLLYWOOD" TAPE, THAT
SOMETHING LIKE THIS COULD BE THE
STRAW TT BROKE THE CAMEL'S
BACK.
>> YOU MIGHT SAY OF COURSE IT
WAS POLITICAL OR WHO CARES, BUT
THIS ALL MATTERS NOW BECAUSE IT
GOES BACK TO THE CRIME THAT
MICHAEL COHEN CONFESSED TO.
DONALD TRUMP CONTINUES TO MOUNT
A DEFENSE CLAIMING THAT THOSE
PAYMENTS WERE PERSONAL AND NOT
POLITICAL, MEANING YOU WOULDN'T
GET IN TROUBLE WITH CAMPAIGN
LAW.
NOW COHEN'S GOING TO JAIL
BECAE HE PLEAD GUILTY TO, YES,
A CAMPAIGN FINANCE VIOLATION,
AND THIS MAN WHO WAS ON THE
OTHER SIDE OF THE TABLE WITH
COHEN, DAVIDSON, ISN'T IN THE
CLEAR EITHER.
CONGRESS WANTS TO HEAR FROM HIM.
HE IS NOW ON THAT NOW FAMOUS
LIST O81 PEOPLE THAT THE HOUSE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE IS
INVESTIGATING.
HE IS ALSO FACING SEPARATE
ALLEGATIONS THAT HE ORIGINALLY
COLLUDED AGAINST HIS OWN CLIENTS
WITH COHEN.
THAT'S A CLAIM DENIES.
WE'VE COVERED IT ON THE SHOW.
BUT IN THIS NEW INTERVIEW, HE IS
DISHING ON HOW FRIENDLY HE AND
COHEN WERE.
DAVIDSON SAYS COHEN CONFIDED IN
HIM ABOUT BEING UPSET THAT HE
DIDN'T EVEN GET, WAIT FOR IT, A
ROLE IN THE WHITE HOUSE, WHICH
OF COURSES ALSO INTERESTING
BECAUSE WHATEVER EVERYONE THINKS
OF MICHAEL COHEN, THIS HAS COME
UP IN WHAT EVERYONE THINKS ABOUT
BEING 100% TRUTHFUL ABOUT.
>> HE CONDED IN ME THAT HE WAS
JUST BESIDE HIMSELF, AND IN HIS
WORDS, HE SAID CAN YOU [ BLEEP ]
EVEN BELIEVE IT.
AFTER EVERYTHING I'VE DONE, HE'S
NOT TAKING ME T WASHINGTON.
>> CAN YOU BELIEVE HIT?
WELL, MANY PEOPLE SAY YEAH YOU
WORK HARD FOR DONALD TRUMP, IT
DOESN'T NECESSARILY GET
RETURNED.
THE HOUSE CENTRAL IS "ACCESS
HOLLYWOOD" TAPE.
A FORMER FOX REPORTER IS ALSO
TRYING TO GET OUT OF AN NDA
AFTER REPORTS THAT FOX KILLED
THE STORY ON THAT BEFORE THE
ELECTION BECAUSE RUPERT MURDOCH
WAS TRYING TO PUT A THUMB ON THE
SCALE AND GET TRUMP TO WIN,
RELEASING A STATEMENT THAT
QUOTE, THE PUBLIC HAS THE RIGHT
TO KNOW THE TRUTH.
FOX NEWS HAS DENIED THIS.
DAVIDSON WEIGHING IN SAYING THE
FOX REPORTER CALLED HIM F
COMMENT RIGHT AFTER THE "ACCESS
HOLLYWOOD" TAPE CAME OUT WITH
FACTUALLY SPECIFIC DETAILST
3450IG9 HAVE INFORMED THAT STORY
WHICH DIDN'T ORIGINALLY RUN.
HERE WITH ME NOW EXCLUSIVELY IS
THE LAWYER FOR THAT FORMER FOX
REPORT, NANCY ERIKA SMITH, A
LEADING CIVIL RIGHTS LAWYER WHO
ALSO REPRESENTED GRETCHEN
CARLSON IN A SEXUAL HARASSMENT
LAWSUIT AGAINST FORMER FOX NEWS
CEO ROGER AILES.
AND FORMER CHIEF COUNSEL OF THE
SENATE WATERGATE COMMITTEE WHO
KNOWS A TNG OR TWO ABOUT
INVESTIGATING POLITICAL CRIMES.
THANKS TO EACH OF YOU FOR BEING
HERE.
NANCY, BEFORE WE GET DEEP INTO
THE DETAILS, WHAT DO YOU THINK
MR. DAVIDSON, WHATEVER HIS
CREDIBILITY, THE CORE OF WHAT
HE'S SAYING, DOES THAT HELP THE
CASE AGAINST TRUMP?
BECAUSE IT SEEMS LIKE ANOTHER
PERSON CORROBORATING THAT THIS
WAS CAMPAIGN-RELATED.
>> IT ABSOLUTELY DOES, AND THE
TIMING DOES AS WELL.
WHEN YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
MID-OCTOBER, WEEKS BEFORE THE
ELECTION, YOU'RE TALKINGBOUT
SOMETHING THAT COULD CLEARLY
AFFECT AN ELECTION.
OBVIOUSLY TRUMP THOUGHT THAT,
AND THERE ARE WITNESSES WHO
SPOKE TO JANE MAYER AT "THE NEW
YORKER"S WHO INDICATE THAT
MURDOCH KNEW THAT AS WELL.
THAT'S WHY THE STORY WAS KILLED
ACCORDING TO JANE MAYER AT "THE
NEW YORKER."
>> ALTHOUGH THEY DENY THAT.
>> THEY DENY IT, BUT THIS IS
ALLY EASY.
THIS IS SIMPLE.
MAYBE CONGRESS SHOULD SUBPOENA
MY CLIENT AND ALL OF HER
RECORDS, AND THEN WE WILL SEE
EXACTLY WHAT FOX NEWS HAD.
>> HAVE YOU AND YOUR CLIENT BEEN
CONTACTED BY SAY, HOUSE
JUDICIARY OR OVERSIGHT?
>> NOT YET.
BUT SUB AENA WILL TRUMP AN
NDA.
>> SO YOU'RE MAKING A LITTLE BIT
OF NEWS HERE, WHICH WHY WE LIKE
EXCLUSIVE GUTS.
YOU'RE SAYING THAT FORMER FOX
NEWS REPORTER, WHICHSY DIANA
FALZONE.
>> UNTIL IT IS VALIDATED BY THE
COURT.
>> OR UNTIL SHE GETS A SUBPOENA.
>> WHICH YOU'RE SAYING WOULD
OVERRIDE IT ANYWAY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> SO YOU'RE SAYING IF WE JUST
HAD A CONGRESSMAN EARLIER IN THE
SHOW.
IF ONE OF THESE CONGRESS PERSONS
WANTED TO SUBPOENA YOUR CLIENT
WITH THE POWER OF THE HOUSE,
THAT WOULD YOU SAY DELIVER WHAT?
WHAT VALUE WOULD THAT ADD?
.
THAT WOULD ADD -- IT WOULD ADD
TO THE INVESTIGATION OF WHETHER
FOX IS REALLY A NEWS
ORGANIZATION OR WHETHER IT IS A
CAMPAIGN ARM OF DONALD TRUMP OR
WHETHER JUST KILLING THE STORY
WAS AN ILLEGAL CAMPAIGN
CONTRIBUTION WORTH WHAT?
OBVIOUSLY THEY THOUGHT IT WAS
WORTH SOMETHING IF IT HAPPENED.
HE WON THE ELECTORAL COLLEGE BY
78,000 VOTES.
WOULD8,000O-CALLED
EVANGELICALS THOUGHT DIFFERENTLY
ABOUT HIM IF THEY KNEW ABOUT AN
AFFAIR AND A PAYOFF STORY WITH A
PORN STAR?
POSSIBLY.
>> I ALMOST GET THE FEELING YOUR
LIKE AN EFFECTIVE LAWYER WITH A
LONG-TERM STRATEGY HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> DAVID, YOU KNOWR WAY
AROUND THE CONGRESSIONAL
INVESTIGATIVE PROCESS.
NANCY KNOWS A LOT, BUT ALSO HAS
A CLIENT HERE, SO SHE HAS AN
AGENDA AND INTEREST.
DO YOU FUNDAMENTALLY THINK IN
YOUR INDEPENDENT ANALYSIS THAT
THIS IS A PROPER A FRUITFUL
AVENUE FOR THE HOUSE DEMOCRATS?
WHAT'S YOUR REACTION TO WHAT SHE
JUST SAID AND THE STORY?
>> WELL, ABSOLUTELY.
I THINK IT'S A VERY IMPORTANT
RT OFHE PICTURE, AND I THINK
IT'S ALSO A VERY IMPORTANT PART
OF THE PICTURE FOR THE SOUTHERN
DISTRICT OF NEW YORK.
AND I THINK THAT'S WHERE THE
ACTION IS GOING TO BE.
FOR ONE REASON, AS A PROSECUTOR,
I COULD GET INCOME TAX RETURNS.
SO THE SOUTHERN DISTRICT OF NEW
YORK MAY BE SITTING THERE WITH
TRUMP'S INCOME TAX RETURNS.
AND WHAT'S GOING ON, WHEN TRUMP
PAID COHEN TO REIMBURSE HIM FOR
THE PAYMENTS TO STORMY DANIELS,
HE LISTED THAT AS A RETAINER AND
PRESUMABLY DEDUCTED THOSE
PAYMENTS.
THAT DEDUCTION --
YOU START TALKING ABOUT TAX EN
DEDUCTION.
>> WELL, IT'S A SUBJECT THAT
FLOORS A LOT OF PEOPLE.
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO DONALD
TRUMP, IT MAY BE PART OF HIS
DOWNFALL BECAUSE HE DEDUCTED
THOSE PAYMENT TO MICHAEL COHEN.
>> BUT IS THIS LIKE -- ARE YOU
BASICALLY IMAGINING AN AL CAPONE
SITUATION WHERE AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED, HE GETS IN
TROUBLE FOR TAX DEDUCTIONS?
>> PERHAPS.
>> BECAUSE FOR ONE THING, TRUMP
COULD PARDON HIMSELF, BUT HE
COULDN'T PARDON HIMSELF FOR
VIOLATING STATE LAW.
AND THE INCOME TAX RETURNS THAT
HE FILED ON BEHALF FOR THE STATE
WOULD BE FALSE BECAUSE HE
PRESUMABLY DEDUCTED THE PAYMENTS
TO MICHAEL COHEN.
>> WELL, DAVID, TAKE A LTEN TO
THE WAY THE WHITE HOUSE IS
HANDLING THIS, DEFLECTING
BASICALLY ON COHEN, A PROBLEM
THAT WON'T SEEM TO GO AWAY.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> WHY DID THE PRESIDENT WRITE A
CHECK TO MICHAEL COHEN FOR
$35,000 IN AUGUST OF 2017?
HE TESTIFIED ABOUT THIS.
HE SPECIFICALLY ACCUSED THE
PRESIDENT OF ENGAGING IN
CONSPIRACY TO ENGAGE IN CAMPAIGN
VIOLATION.
>> THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN CLEAR
THERE WASN'T A CAMPAIGN
VIOLATION.
>> DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT THE HUSH
MONEY.
THE STORY HAS CHANGED.
>> AGAIN, I WOULD REFER YOU BACK
TO THE PRESIDENT'S COMMENTS.
>> DAVID, YOUR VIEW OF THEIR
STRUGGLE TO EVEN EXPLAIN WHAT IS
CORROBORATED, WHICH IS THESE
PAYMENTS FOR, AGAIN, AN NDA THAT
THEY LITERALLY SUEDRMY OVER
WHICH WAS THEIR WAY OF
CORROBORATING THEY PAID FOR IT.
>> WELL, I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT
BECAUSE THE PAYMENTS ARE
DOCUMENTED NOW WITH CHECKS.
I THINK THEY'RE DOING
GOBBLEDYGOOK, AS IN WATERGATE
WHERE HUSH MONEY WAS AN
IMPORTANT PART OF THE PICTURE
AND ULTIMATELY I THINK WAS THE
DOWNFALL OF A PART OF THE
COVER-UP, I THINK THESE PAYMENTS
ARE GOING TO BE VERY, VERY
IMPORTANT.
>> INTERESTING.
AND THAT'S INTERESTING COMING
FROM YOUR WATERGATE EXPERIENCE
AND SDNY.
NANCY, I DO WANT TO MAKE SURE
WE'RE CLEAR HERE BECAUSE THIS IS
A DISPUTE.
I WANT TO READ WHAT A FOX
EXE SAYS ABOUT THIS, WHICH
IS, QUOTE, DANIELS AND HER
ASSOCIATES WERE ACTUALLY PLAYING
A BIZARRE CAT AND MOUSE NEWS
GAME WITH FOX AND OTHER NEWS
TLETS, TRYING TO GET THEIR
STORY OUT, WITHOUT FINGERPRINTS
AND ULTIMATELY WITHOUT ENOUGH
PROOF T PUBLISH.
ISN'T THAT A FAIR DEFENSE FOR
JOURNALISTIC OUTLETS WHO SAID
THEY NEEDED TO BE SURE BEFORE
THEY WENT WITH SOMETHING?
>> JOURNALISTIC OUTLETS WOULDN'T
HAVE TO KEEP THE STO UNDER AN
NDA IF THEY WANTED THE STORY TO
COME OUT.
AND PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES
SHOULD NOT BE ABLE HIDE
INFORMATION FROM THE AMERICAN
PUBLIC WITH NDAs.
>> SO YOU'RE SAYING IF THAT
DEFENSE IS TRUE IT MIGHT BE
VALID, AND YOUR FORMAL
ENTINT SHEER NOT THAT THEY
DON'T HAVE A GOOD ARGUMENT TO
DISCUSS, BUT THAT THEY'RE
ACTUALLY TRYING TO PREVENT THE
DISCUSSION OF THAT.
>> ABSOLUTELY, THAT'S EXACTLY --
>> THAT MAKES A GOOD POINT.
AND I THINK THE POINT YOU MAKE
ABOUT THE HOUSE IS ABSOLUTELY
INTERESTING.
NANCY ERIKA SMITH AND DAVID
DORIS SENN, THANKS TO BOTH OF
YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> UP NEXT, MAKING WAVES ABOUT
WHAT LIBERAL VOTER THINKS OFHE
SOCIALIST AGENDA.
AOC SOUNDING OFF.
AND LATER COMEDY IN THE TRUMP
ERA AND MORE WITH THE MAN BEHIND
"SEINFELD."
>> EXCUSE ME, I THINK YOU FORGOT
MY BREAD.
>> BREAD $2 EXTRA.
>> 2?
BUT EVERYONE IN FRONT OF MEOT
FREE BREAD.
>> YOU WANT BREAD?
>> YES.
>> $3!
NO SOUP FOR YOU.
of life
into our Subaru Forester.
(DAD)
It's good to be back.
(MOM)
It sure is.
(MOM VO)
Over the years, we trusted
it to carry and protect
the things that were most
important to us.
We always knew we had a lot of
life ahead of us.
(MOM)
Remember this?
(MOM VO)
That's why we chose a car that
we knew would be there for us
through it all.
(The longest-lasting, most
Wtrusted Forester ever.2019
Subaru Forester.
Do your asthma symptoms
ever hold you back?
About 50% of people with
severe asthma
have too many cells called
eosinophils in their lungs.
Eosinophils are a key
cause of severe asthma.
FASENRA is desned to tget
and remove these cells.
FASENRA is an add-on
injection for people 12
and up with asthma
driven by sinophils.
FASENRA is not a rescue
medicine
or for other
eosinophilic conditions.
FASENRA is proven to help
prevent severe asthma attacks,
improve breathing, and can
lower oral steroid use.
FASENRA may cause
alrgic reactions.
Get help right away if you
have swelling of your
face, mouth, and tongue, or
trouble breathing.
Don't stop your asthma
treatments
unless your doctor
tells you to.
Tell your doctor if you have a
parasitic infection
or your asthma worsens.
Headache and sore throat may
occur.
Haven't you missed enough?
Ask an asthma specialist
about FASENRA.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may
be able to help.
My experience with USAA
has been excellent.
They really appreciate
thmilitary family
and it really shows.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
It was funny because
when we wocall
another insurance company,
hey would say
“Oh we can't beat USAA”
We're bber family.
We're the Tenney's
We're the Hayles,
and we're USAA members for life.
♪
Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
>>> FOR A HUGE SHAKE-UP IN THE
TECH SECTOR.
>> IT'S BIG AND IT'S BOLD AND
IT'S GOING TO BE DIFFICULT TO
ACHIEVE.
>> COULD SHE REALLY FORCE THIS
KIND OF BREAKUP?
>> COULD SHE REALLY DO IT?
>> YOU BET.
>> WHAT'S THE ANSWER?
>> THE ANSWER IS YES.
>> YES.
THAT WAS SENATOR ELIZABETH
WAENIG HERE ON FRIDAY
NIGHT.
SHE'S GOT A SWEEPING PLAN THAT
SHE WAS UNVEILING TO TRY TO
BREAK UP THESE POPULAR TECH
GIANTS LIKE GOOGLE AND AMAZON,
AND NOW SHE IS TAKING HER
MESSAGO SNTETHING OF A
PROVERBIAL TECH LIONS DEN
BECAUSE SHE WENT TO ONE OF THE
LEADING TECH CONFERENCES IN THE
NATION IN TEXAS, YOU MAY HAVE
HEARD OF IT, SOUTH BY SOUTHWEST.
AND SO DID FIVE OTHER DEMOCRATIC
HOPEFULS IN 2020.
LET'S GET RIGHT TO IT, MARA GAY,
EDITORIAL BOARD MEMBER FORE
NEW YORK TIMES."
NICE TO SEE YOU.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> THEY ALL GO DOWN THERE
BECAUSE THIS IS ONE OF THE NEW
SCHOOL PLACES TO GATHER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT SENATOR
BEING THE ONE WITH KIND
OF THE TOUGHEST TECH AGENDA IN
THIS TECH SPACE?
>> I THINK IT'S A SMART PLAY FOR
HER POLITICALLY.
I THINK THERE IS A LOT OF ANGER
OVER THESE TECH COMPANIES BEING
UNREGULATED, AND I THINK THEY'VE
BEEN MAKING THE ARGUMENT FOR A
LONG TIME THEY'VE -- THEY'RE THE
BIG INTERRUPTERS.
THEY'RE KIND OF TRYING TO BE
GOOD CITIZENS IN A WAY THAT MOST
CORPORATIONS DON'T PORT TEND TO
BE, REALLY.
AND I THINK THEY'RE KIND OF
ASKING FOR IT IN A SENSE.
AND SO THIS IS A MOMENT WHEN
THERE IS A LOT OF ANGER FROM
THEIR LACK OF ACTION THAT THEY
TOOK.
FACEBOOK, FOR EXAMPLE, IN THE
2016 ELECTION DOWN TO AMAZON
HAVING CITIES COMPETE.
>> RIGHT.
>> TO GIVE THEM, YOU KNOW, A
CORPORATE GIVEAWAYS.
>> AND PEOPLE DON'T TEND TO
THINK OF MOST CORPORATIONS AS
RED OR BLUE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> BUT BEFORE THESE -- WHA
YOU'RE DEFINING AS THESE 2016
SCANDALS, THE TECH SECTOR WAS
CONSIDERED SOMEWHAT CLOSE TO THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY, WAS CONSIDERED
SORT OF NEW SCHOOL.
AMAZON WAS NOT CONSIRED EXXON,
IT'S FAIR TO SAY.
AS YOU POINT OUT, THAT MAY BE
CHANGING.
THIS IS HER IN RAPID-FIRE WHEN I
ASKED HER IN A WORD TO DEFINE
THESE COMPANIES AND A FEW OTHER
THINGS.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> SURE.
>> AMAZON.
>> TOO BIG.
>> GOOGLE.
>> FACEBOOK.
>> TOO BIG.
>> MARK ZUCKERBERG.
>> TOO POWERFUL.
>> FAVORITE MEMBER OF THE
FEDERAL RESERVE BOARD OF
VERNORS?
>> OH, JANET YELLEN.
>> YOUR DREAM RUNNING MATE
THROUGHOUT HISTORY, LIVE
ORGANIZE DEAD, IF YOU COULD PICK
A PERSON THAT WOULD RUN WITH
YOU.
>> TEDDY ROOSEVELT.
>> AND SHE CITED TEDDY, WHO
HAPPENS TO BE REPUBLICAN FOR
TAKING ON THE BIG CORPORATIONS.
>> THE TRUST BUSTER.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
HOW MUCH OF THIS COULD BE THE
FAULT LINE OF THE DEMOCRA
PRIMARY?
>> LISTEN, IT'S A WARNING SHOT.
I THINK ACTUALLY THAT THE REAL
FAULT LINE OFHE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY IS GOING TO BE AND THE
CENTRAL QUESTION FOR DEMOCRATIC
VOTERS AND OTHER VOTERS IS GOING
TO BE HOW THESE CANDIDATES DEAL
WITH NOT JUST DONALD TRUMP BUT
ALSO INCOME INEQUALITY.
AND THE TECH SECTOR CERTAINLY
PLAYS INTO THAT, AMAZON IN SOME
WAY ABSOLUTELY.
BUT I DON'T SEE THIS AS THE
CENTRAL ISSUE NECESSARILY OF THE
ELECTION.
>> AND BEFORE I LET YOU GO,
SPEAKER PELOSI SAYING VERY
CLY WE'RE NOT ON OUR WAY TO
IMPEACHING HIM.
THE GRASSROOTS AND SOME OF THE
2020 CANDIDATES SEEM TO BE
STRIKING A DIFFERENT CHORD.
>> LO, THE CASE FOR
IMPEACHMENT SHOULD BE -- THE BAR
FOR IMPEACHMENT, EXCUSE ME,
SHOULD BE EXTREMELY HIGH.
IT'S A DRASTIC MOVE.
BUT I THINK WHEN YOU HAVE
MICHAEL COHEN, THE PRESIDENT'S
FORMER LAWYERMPLICATING THE
PRESIDENT IN POTENTIALLY A DOZEN
CRIMES, WE'VE CROSSDELINE THAT
DEMANDS A SERIOUS CONSIDERATION,
AND WE CAN WAIT FOR THE MUELLER
REPORT TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS, BUT
I THINK -- I THINK, YOU KNOW,
SPEAKER PELOSI IS GOING TO BE IN
A TOUGH PLACE AND SHE IS TRYING
TO GIVE HERSELF TIME, AND THAT'S
JUST FINE.
>> RIGHT.
AS YOU SAY, I THINK WHAT SHE WAS
SAYING AND CONGRESSMAN JEFFRIES
IS ALLUDING TO THIS NIGHT THEY
DON'T WANT TO BE MARCHED INTO IT
BEFORE THEY EVEN FIND OUT WHAT
MUELLER HAS.
I'M SURE THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE,
AND WE'VE INTERVIEWED THEM WHO
SAY SHE HAS GONE TOO FAR IN
BUYING TIME.
>> IF THE PRESIDENTS GUILTY OF
SYSTEM OF THE THINGS THAT HE HAS
BEEN ACCUSED OF DOING, THEN SOME
OF THESE ALLEGATIONS ARE
IMPEHABLE OFFENSES.
>> RIGHT.
AND SO THE QUESTION THEN AS THEY
PUT IT, DO THEY WAIT FOR THE
SENATE AND SAY WE DON'T HAVE A
CAUSE.
THAT'S WHAT WAS JEFFREYS'
ARGUMENT TONIGHT OR DO YOU HAVE
AN OBLIGATION TO DEAL WITH IT.
THAT'S A CONVERSATION THAT WILL
KEEP ROLLING.
.
ANK YOU TONIGHT.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>>> THE MAN BEHIND "SEINFELD"
AND "CURB," AND A LOT MOTHER SAT
THE TABLE, COMING UP.
TABLE,OMINP
So, we re-imagined the razor
with the new Gillette SkinGuard.
It has a unique guard
between the blades.
That's designed to reduce
irritation during the shave.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
llet   Gi.
HUMIRA patients,
you inspire us.
The way you triumph
over adversity.
And live your lives.
That's why we redesigned HUMIRA.
We wanted to make
the experien
better for you.
Now there's less
pain immediately
following injection.
We've reduced the size
of the needle
and removed the
citrate buffers.
And it has the same
effectiveness you
know and trust.
HUMIRA Citrate-free is here.
A little change can make
a big difference.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections,
including tuberculosis, and
cancers, including lymphoma,
have happened, as have blood,
liver, and nervous system
problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas where certain
fung infections are common
d if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't starHUMIRA i
you have an infection.
Ask your doctor
about HUMIRA
Citrate-free.
Here's to you.
[farmers bell]
(Driver)
Relax, it's just a bug.
That not a bug,
that's not a bug!
(Burke)
Hit and Drone.
Seen it, covered it.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
If you have moderate to severe
plaque psoriasis,
every day can begin with flakes.
It's a reminder of your
struggles with psoriasis.
But what if your
psoriasis symptoms
didn't follow you around?
That's why there's ILUMYA.
With just 2 Doses,
a majority of people were clear
or almost clear.
And over time, even more people
were clear or almost clear.
All with dosing 4 times
a year...
after 2 initial doses.
Plus, ILUMYA was shown to have
similar risks of infections
compared to placebo.
n't use if you are
allergic to ILUMYA
or any of its ingredients.
Before starting treatment,
your doctor should check for
tuberculosis and infections.
After checking there is no need
for routine lab monitoring
unless your doctor advises it.
ILUMYA may increase your
risk of infections
and lower your ability
to fight them.
Tell your doctor if you have an
infection or have symptoms,
or if you plan to or have
recently received a vaccine.
This could be your chance
to leave your psoriasis
symptoms behind.
Ask your doctor for ILUMYA
today, for a clearer tomorrow.
Before discovering Nexium 24HR
to treat his frequent heartburn,
Steven could only imagine
enjoying a spicy taco.
Now, his world
explodes with flavor.
Nexium 24Hops
acid before it starts
for all-day all-night
protection.
Can you imagine -hours
without heartburn?
>>> IF YOU WATCH "THE BEAT," YOU
KNOW THAT SOMETIMES WE TRY TO BE
FUNNY ON THIS SHOW, WHICH RARELY
WORKS OUT.
BUT TONIGHT WE'RE GOING TO GET
SOME HELP FROM LARRY CHARLES,
THE WRITER FOR THE HIT TV SITCOM
"SEINFELD," WHERE HE EARNED AN
EMMY.
HE ALSO WENT ON THEIRECT LARRY
DAVID'S HBO SERIES "CURB YOUR
ENTHUSIASM," PLUS THE FAMOUS
DOCUMENTARY "BORAT" PLUS NOW HE
HAS "LARRY CHARLES, DANGEROUS
WORLD OF COMEDY" WHERE HE
EMBARKS ON A MISSION AROUND THE
WORLD TO LOOK AT WHAT MAKES US
LAUGH.
THE WORLD OF COMEDY IS NOT
JUST ABOUT COMEDIANS, IT'S ALSO
ABOUT THE PEOPLE THAT MAKE IT A
DANGEROUS WORLD, MURDERERS,
TERRORIST, EXTREMISTS AND WHAT
THEY LAUGH AT.
WE WILL EXPLORE COMEDY IN PLACES
WHERE NOTHING THE FUNNY, IN
PLACES WHERE IT DOESN'T BELONG.
BY KNOWING A COUNTRY'S COMEDY,
YOU WILL  ITS PAST, PRESENT,
AND FUTURE.
>> THANKS FOR BEING HERE, LARRY.
>> MY PLEASURE.
THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>> FOR HAVING ME.
>> COMEDY AS A WINDOW INTO THE
SOUL.
>> YES.
>> THAT'S SOMETHING YOU BELIEVE
THE OR JUST YOUR PITCH TO
NETFLIX?
>> KIND OF SOMETHING I LEARNED.
I CAME IN THINKING I WOULD MEET
PEOPLE DOING WHAT THE DAILY SHOW
DOES HERE.
SATIRIING CORRUPT GOVERNMENTS
AND TRYIN TO SURVIVE.
THAT DOES EXIST IN GREAT NURMS
-- NUMBERS AROUND THE WORLD.
COMEDY ALSO HEALS.
PEOPLE DYING AND BEING WOUNDED
AND INJURED.
FAMILIES BEING DESTROYED AND
LAUGHTER BEING USED AS A TOOL
FOR HEALING.
>> BECAUSE SEINFELD WAS SO
BELOVED.
IT WAS ONE OF THE LAST SHOWS
THAD REALLY THE WHOLE
COUNTRY TUNING IN.
ITS JOKES WERE SEEN AS ABOUT
EVERY ONE SAID NOTHING.
IT WAS MORE THAN THAT BUT ABOUT
STUFF WE CAN ALL RELATE TO
INCLUDING THE LITTLE STUFF.
WHAT IS THE DEAL WITH AIRPLANE
FOOD?
>> I'M NOT IF NOT HOPELESSLY
DERIVATIVE.
YOU WORK WITH LARRY DAVID.
>> YES.
>> WE ARE ALL IN POLITICS
GETTING READY TO SEE MORE LARRY
DAVID BECAUSE BERNIE SANDERS IS
BACK.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THIS ICONIC
IMPRESSION.
>> PEOPLE LOVE ME.
I HAVE MORE INDIVIDUAL DONATIONS
THAT ANY CANDIDATE IN HISTORY
AND I DON'T TAKE FROM
MILLIONAIRES ANDBILLIONAIRES.
>> WE KNOW.
YOU SAY IT EVERY TIME YOU'RE ON
TV.
EVERYBODY KNOWS.
>> DOES THAT COUNT AS AN
IMPRESSION OR IS THAT JUST LARRY
DAVID?
>> I THINK LARRY DAVID IS SO
UNIQUELY QUALIFIED FOR THAT
IMPRESSION IT'S NOT MUCH OF A
LEAP.
BERNIE IS FROM THE SAME
NEIGHBORHOOD AS WE ARE.
WE GREW UP WITHUYS LIKE BERNIE
SANDERS ALL OVER THE PLACE.
>> D YOU EVER THINK ONE OF
THEM WOULD GET THIS FAR IN
POLITICS?
>> I GREW UP IN TRUMP VILLAGE.
AS MUCH AS I'M STILL GETTING
OVERERNIE SANDERS, TRUMP BEING
PRESIDENT IS SOMETHING I'LL
NEVER GET USED TO.
>> TRUMP VILLAGEAS BUILT BY H
HIS FATHER.
HE WAS LIKE A 14-YEAR-OLD KILL
STILL IN A SUIT WANDER AROUND
THE HAIR.
HE WANTS TO BE A COMEDIAN.
HE THINKS HE'S FUNNY AND HOW HE
HAS A CAPTIVE AUDIENCE WHICH IS
DANGEROUS.
>> BEFORE I LET YOU GO, I WANT
TO PLAY SOME OF YOUR WORK TO DO
SOMETHING THAT NO ONE IS ASKING
FOR WHICH WAS TRY TO MAKE
HOLOCAUST SURVIVAL HUMORIST.
PEOPLE HAVE STRONG OPINIONS ONE
WAY OR THE OTHER AND YOU ARE
JEWISH.
>> RIGHT.
>> LET'S TAKE LOOK AT THIS
CLIP.
>> HAVE YOU EVER SEEN THE SHOW?
>> DID YOU EVER SEE OUR SHOW?
IT WAS CALLED THE HOLOCAUST.
ALL I KNOW IS I WAS CLOSE TO
THAT MILLION DOLLARS.
EVERY ONE WAS TRYING TO KICK ME
OFF THE SHOW.
>> I'M A SURVIVOR.
I'M A SURVIVOR.
>> I'M A SURVOR.
>> FUNNY.
>> FUNNY?
IF IT BENDS IT'S FUY.
>> IT'S NOT REALLY EXPLOITING
THE HOLOCAUST.
>> WHO IS THE TARGET OF THE
JOKE?
>> THE TARGET IS THE GUY ON
SURVIVOR.
THE IDEA THAT HE WOULD HAVE NO
SENSE OF WHAT THE HOLOCAUST AND
HAVE A COMPETITIVE CONVERSATION
WITH THE SURVIVOR SHOWS HOW
OBLIVIOUS SHE.
IT'S COMPLETELY FUNNY AND
RELATABLE.
>> ISN'T THERE THE OLD SAYING,
IN YOU'RE IGNORANT OF HISTORY,
YOU'RE DESTINED TO BE MADE FUN
OF ON A PREMIUM CABLE SHOW?
>> THAT'S HOW IT WORKS.
>> I'M ASKING THE QUESTIONS
HERE.
SATIRE VIOLENCE.
WHAT'S MORE BITING THAN SATIRE?
>> YOU'RE A BIT LIKE ANDY McCAB.
DN'T WANT TO ANSWER, HE
WOULD REPEAT THE QUESTION BACK
OR SAY WHAT ARE YOU REALLY
ASKING.
>> I'M WAITING FOR MUELLER
REPORT ALSO.
>> LARRY CHARLES, I THINK YOU
HAVE THAT IN COMMON WITH MANY
PEOPLE.
WHEN YOU LOOK A  COMEDY, IS IT A
HELPFUL PART TO GET THROUGH OF
WHAT YOU CALL A ROUGH PERIOD OR
JUST AERSION
COMEDY IS LIKE BREATHING AND
EATING.
LAUGHTER IS A CRUCIAL PART OF
SURVIVAL.
I THINK IT'S VERY IMPORTANT
SUBJECT AND SOM WE NEED
MORE THAN EVER NOW.
>> LARRY CHARLES.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ALL RIG
HT
That rocking chair wldk
great in our new house.
Ahh, New house, eh?
Well, you should definitely see
how GEICO
could help you save on
homeowners insurance.
Nice tip. I'll give tw
Wait wait... how did that get
out here?
That is definitely not for sale!
Is this a yard sale?
If it's in the yard then it's...
for sale.
Oh, here we go.
GEICO. It's easy to switch
and save
homeowns and renters
insurance.
Let's see, ALEVE is
proven better on pain
than Tylenol Extra Strength.
And last longer
with fewer pills.
So why am I still
thinking about this?
I'll take Aleve.
ALEVE.
ProStaying at Hampton.
for a work trip.
Oh no.
Your new boss
seems cool,
but she might not
be sweatpants cool.
Not quite ready
to face the day?
That's why we're here
with free hot breakfast.
Book at Hampton.com for
our Price Match Guarantee.
Hampton by Hilton.
Ways to lose stubborn belly fat:
Book at Hampton.com for
The Chili Peppweat-Out.ee.
cool.
Freezing away fat cells with
CoolSculpting?
Now that's cool!
CoolSculpting safely freezes and
removes fat cells
with little or no downtime.
And no surgery.
Results and patient experience
may vary.
Some common side effects include
temporary numbss,
discomfort, and swelling.
Ask your doctor if CoolSculpting
is right for you.
And visit CoolSculpting.com
today
I switched to MiraLAX
for my constipation.
for your chance to win a free
treatment.
Stimulant laxatives
forcefully stimulate
the nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX works with
the water in your
body to unblock your
system naturally.
And itsn't cause
bloating,
cramping, gas,
or sudden urgency.
♪ Like a fool I
went and stayed
too long. ♪
♪ Now I'm wondering if your
loves still strong. ♪
MiraLAX.
Look for the pink cap.
♪ Ooo baby, here I am, signed,
sealed, delivered, I'm yours ♪
Applebee's
3 Course Meal
Now that's
Eatin' Good
in the Neighborhood.
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
♪♪
You should be mad they gave this
guy a promotion.
You should be mad at
forced camaraderie.
And you should be mad at tech
that makes things worse.
But you're not mad,
because you have E*TRADE,
who's tech makes life easier
by automatically adding
technical patterns on charts
and helping you understand what
they mean.
Don't get mad.
Get E*TRADE's simplified
technical analysis.