LAST FOUR YEARS SINCE THE LAST
ONE.
WHAT CAN WE DO TO MAKE OURSELVES
BETTER AND PUT OURSELVES IN THE
BEST POSITION?
>> THERE YOU GO.
ENTIRE COUNTRY IS ROOTING FOR
THOSE WOMEN.
THE WHITE HOUSE JUST ANNOUNCED
THEY'RE SENDING A DELEGATION
OVER TO THE GAME IN FRANCE LED
BY THE DEPARTMENT COMMERCE OF
SECRETARY AND OTHERS.
IT'S GOING TO BE A GOOD ONE.
THANK YOU FOR COMING ON THE SHOW
AND THANK YOU ALL FOR WATCHING
THIS HOUR OF MSNBC LIVE.
CRAIG, WHERE ARE YOU WATCHING
THE GAME?
>> GO TEAM USA.
I'LL BE WATCHING FROM THE COMFY
CONFINES OF MY BASEMENT.
>> VERY NICE.
BIG SCREEN.
LOVE IT.
>> CRAIG MEDICAL SIN HERE, MSNBC
HEADQUARTERS NEW YORK CITY.
TANKS IN POSITION, PREPARATIONS
UNDER WAY FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
BIG FOURTH OF JULY EVENT,
INCLUDING THOSE MILITARY
VEHICLES NOW ON THE NATIONAL
MALL AS NEW DETAILS ABOUT HOW
IT'S BEING PAID FOR ARE
GENERATING MORE FURRY.
ALSO HAWKEYE SWING.
2020 CANDIDATES MAKING THEIR WAY
TO IOWA FOR THE HOLIDAY AS A NEW
POLL OF VOTERS IN THAT STATE
REVEALS SOME NEW CHALLENGES FOR
SOME OF THOSE CONTENDERS.
TWO OF THE DEMOCRATIC CONTENDERS
WILL JOIN ME LIVE THIS HOUR.
TWO OF THEM.
>>> ALSO, TICKING TIME BOMB.
THAT IS HOW ONE OFFICIAL IN A
NEW GOVERNMENT WATCHDOG REPORT
DESCRIBES THE HORRIFIC
CONDITIONS INSIDE MIGRANT
DETENTION FACILITIES.
IT INCLUDES SHOCKING NEW IMAGES
FROM INSIDE.
WE'LL GET TO THAT STORY IN JUST
A MOMENT.
BUT WE START WITH THOSE TANKS
AND MILITARY VEHICLES DESCENDING
ON THE NATIONAL MALL FOR
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S SELF-PRODUCED
FOURTH OF JULY EVENT TOMORROW.
IN A BREAK FROM TRADITION, THE
PRESIDENT HAS ORDER A DISPLAY OF
AMERICAN MILITARY MIGHT IN THE
CAPITAL THAT.
PLAN, ITS MEANING, AND ITS COST
ALL STIRRING CONTROVERSY.
JOINING ME NOW, NEW HAMPSHIRE'S
MONICA ALBA LIVE ON THE NATIONAL
MALL.
ASHLEY PARKER WHITE HOUSE
REPORTER FOR THE "WASHINGTON
POST."
AN MSNBC SENIOR POLITICAL
ANALYST.
DEMOCRATIC CONGRESSMAN DON BAIRD
IS WITH ME, HIS DISTRICT
INCLUDES NORTH VIRGINIA.
AND "WASHINGTON POST" OPINION
RATE WRITER JENNIFER REUBEN AND
MARK, PRESIDENTIAL HORN AND
PRESIDENT AND CEO OF THE LBJ
FOUNDATION.
QUITE ESTEEMED PANEL HERE.
MONICA, I'LL START WITH YOU.
WHAT ARE WE SEEING THERE ON THE
MALL TODAY?
>> SO, CRAIG, ACTUALLY IF I TURN
HERE YOU'RE GOING TO SEE TWO
BRADLEY FIGHTING VEHICLES.
AND THESE ARE JUST SOME OF THE
MILITARY MIGHT THAT'S GOING TO
BE ON DISPLAY TOMORROW EVENING.
THIS IS, OF COURSE, BEING
TRANSPORTED ON SUCH A LARGE
FLATBED BECAUSE OF HOW HEAVY
THEY ARE.
THE ABRAMS TANKS WHICH ARE OTHER
TANKS PARKED NEARBY AND GOING TO
BE ON THE MALL WEIGH AS MUCH AS
60 TONS.
YOU CAN IMAGINE THAT'S SOMETHING
THAT COULD DAMAGE D.C. STREETS
AND SOME OF THE PRESIDENT'S
CRITICS HAVE EXPRESSED CONCERN
ABOUT THAT.
BUT THAT'S WHAT THE PRESIDENT
WANTS ON DISPLAY.
HE WANTS TO DO THE SALUTE TO
AMERICA AND FEATURE ALL OF THESE
DIFFERENT MILITARY VEHICLES
AFTER BEING INSPIRED TWO YEARS
AGO AT THE BASTILLE DAY
CELEBRATIONS IN PARIS WHERE HE
SAW THE PARADE WITH PRESIDENT
EMMANUEL MACRON AND SAID I WOULD
VERY MUCH LIKE TO DO THIS.
HE THEN THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO
BE TAKING PLACE ON VETERANS DAY,
BUT THAT GOT CANCELED, YOU MAY
REMEMBER, AND MOVED TO THE
FOURTH OF JULY BECAUSE OF HOW
EXPENSIVE IT IS.
"THE WASHINGTON POST" IS
REPORTING THAT IT'S GOING TO BE
AT LEAST 2.5 MILLION IN ENTRANCE
FEES REDIRECTED TO ACCOUNT FOR
THE EVENT TOMORROW.
AND OF COURSE WE DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE COST IS YET OF THE OTHER
MILITARY FLYOVERS.
THE PRESIDENT HAS TWEETED THAT A
LOT OF THAT IS GOING TO BE FREE
BECAUSE WE OWNERSHIP THE
EQUIPMENT.
BUT YOU HAVE TO THINK ABOUT THE
SECURITY AND OTHER CONCERNS,
OTHER THINGS THAT ARE GOING TO
KIND OF PUT THAT PRICE TAG UP
HIGH.
AND WE DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH
THAT'S GOING TO COST.
NOW, THESE TANKS AND MILITARY
VEHICLES ARE GOING TO BE MOVED.
WE DON'T KNOW EXACTLY WHEN,
WE'RE JUST STEPS FROM THE
LINCOLN MEMORIAL.
BUT THEY'RE ALL GOING TO BE
PLACED UP AND DOWN THE MALL, BUT
WE DON'T KNOW EXACTLY HOW MANY
THERE WILL BE.
AND TOMORROW A LOT OF THE
EXCITEMENT IS AROUND OF COURSE
THE MILITARY FLYOVERS AND WHAT'S
EXPECT TO BE A FLYOVER OF THE
AIR FORCE ONE.
BUT THAT'S THE SCENE FROM HERE
THE DAY BEFORE.
>> MONICA, THANK YOU.
ASHLEY, YOUR PAPER REPORTING
THAT THE NATIONAL PARK SERVICE
IS DIVERTING $2.5 MILLION IN
PARK FEES TO PAY FOR THIS.
THE STORY ADDS, QUOTE, THE
DIVERTED PARK FEES REPRESENT
JUST A FRACTION OF THE EXTRA
COSTS THE GOVERNMENT FACES AS A
RESULT OF THE EVENT WHICH WILL
INCLUDE DISPLAYS OF MILITARY
HARDWARE, FLYOVERS BY JETS
INCLUDING AIR FORCE ONE, THE
DEPLOYMENT OF TANKS ON THE MALL,
AND AN EXTENDED PYROTECHNIC
SHOW.
IS THERE A CONCERN AT THE WHITE
HOUSE OF JUST THE SHEER OPTICS
OF SPENDING SO MUCH MONEY ON
THIS EXTRAVAGANZA AT THAT POINT?
>> WELL, THERE'S CERTAINLY NOT A
CONCERN FROM THE PRESIDENT.
THIS IS WHAT HE WANTS.
BUT YOU CAN SEE IN THAT TWEET HE
SENT THAT HE IS CERTAINLY AWARE
OF THE CRITICISM.
THAT'S SOMETHING THE WHITE HOUSE
HAS BEEN VERY COGNIZANT OF WHEN
THE POST FIRST REPORTED, I
BELIEVE, THAT THERE WERE GOING
TO BE SORT OF A LONGER FIREWORKS
DISPLAY THAN USUAL BECAUSE SOME
COMPANIES HAD VOLUNTEERED TO
HELP WITH THAT.
ONE THING THAT THE WHITE HOUSE
REALLY TRIED TO MAKE CLEAR WAS
THAT, YOU KNOW, THESE WERE SORT
OF NOT QUITE FREE FIREWORKS SHOW
BUT AT A REDUCED RATE AND THAT
THE PRESIDENT WOULD SORT OF BE
FOOLISH NOT TO TAKE THESE
COMPANIES UP ON THE OFFER.
SO THEY'RE AWARE OF THIS
CRITICISM.
AND KEEP IN MIND, YOU MENTIONED
THIS EARLIER, BUT THE WHOLE
REASON THAT HIS PLANS FOR A
VETERANS' DAY PARADE WERE
SCUTTLED WAS BECAUSE THE PRICE
TAG GOT TO ABOUT 90 MILLION.
IT WAS JUST WAY TOO HIGH, THERE
WAS A TON OF OUTCRY INCLUDING
THE D.C. GOVERNMENT, IT WAS NOT
FEASIBLE.
THE PRESIDENT MAY NOT CARE,
NECESSARILY, HE'S CLEARLY
PROCEEDING FULL STEAM AHEAD.
BUT THAT TWEET SHOWS IN OTHER
CONVERSATIONS WE'VE HAD WITH THE
WHITE HOUSE SHOWS THAT THEY ARE
AT LEAST AWARE THAT THERE IS A
NUMBER -- THERE'S A LOT OF
CRITICISM COMING FROM ALL SIDES.
>> ASHLEY, WHAT ELSE DO WE KNOW
ABOUT THIS REPORTING ON THE
REPUBLICAN NATIONAL COMMITTEE
THEY RECEIVED A NUMBER OF VIP
TICKETS THAT THEY'RE HANDING OUT
AS WELL.
ARE THEY HANDING OUT TICKETS TO
A TAX-PAYER FUNDED EVENT?
>> WELL, THERE'S CONCERN --
THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF FAIR
CRITICISM ABOUT THAT FOR SORT OF
POLITICIZING, YOU KNOW, ONE OF
THESE RARE THINGS IN THE NATION
THAT IS APOLITICAL, A HOLIDAY
THAT IS SYMBOLIC AND ABOUT
FIREWORKS AND SPENDING TIME WITH
FAMILIES AND BARBECUES.
THEY'VE TRIED TO ARGUE THIS IS
NO DIFFERENT THAN SOMETIMES
TICKETS ARE HANDED OUT FOR SAY
THE EASTER EGG ROLL OR SOMETHING
ELSE ON THE SOUTH LAWN.
BUT THE OTHER THING THAT IS
WORTH MENTIONING THAT WE'RE
HEARING IS THERE'S ALSO A LOT OF
KIND OF QUIET CHATTER IN THE
PRESIDENT'S ORBIT THAT THEY'RE
DEEPLY WORRIED ABOUT ANOTHER
INAUGURATION FIASCO.
>> NO ONE'S GOING TO SHOW UP.
>> THAT THE PRESIDENT'S CROWDS
WERE NOT AS BIG AS HIS
PREDECESSORS, EXACTLY, NO ONE
WILL SHOW UP.
WHAT HAPPENS IF IT RAINS?
PEOPLE IN A DEEPLY BLUE DISTRICT
WHO ARE NOT FANS OF THE
PRESIDENT ARE FLEEING TOWN.
PART OF THAT IT SEEMS IS
DESIGNED TO KIND OF ENSURE THAT
AT LEAST FOR THE CAMERA SHOT
THAT IT LOOKS LIKE IT IS PACKED
AND THERE'S NOT THESE SORT OF
SPLOTCHES OF GREEN GRASS WHERE
THE PRESIDENT WANTS A HUGE CROWD
BEHIND HIM CELEBRATING HIM.
>> MARK, GIVE US SOME
PERSPECTIVE HERE.
HOW UNUSUAL IS IT TO HAVE A
MILITARY DISPLAY AND FOR A
PRESIDENT TO SPEAK FROM THE MALL
IN THE WAY THAT HE IS REPORTEDLY
GOING TO ON INDEPENDENCE DAY?
UNPRECEDENTED OR NOT?
>> WELL, LIKE ALMOST EVERYTHING
THIS PRESIDENT DOES, THIS IS
UNPRECEDENTED.
THIS IS THE KIND OF MILITARY
DISPLAY WE WERE USED TO SEEING
FROM THE SOVIET UNION ON MAY
DAY.
THIS IS NOT WHAT WE DO AS A
NATION.
WE HAVE FIREWORKS AND PARADES,
BUT WE DON'T SHOW OUR MILITARY
HARDWARE TO THE NATION AND TO
THE WORLD.
I THINK THIS IS A PRESIDENT WHO
VERY MUCH WANTS TO BE SEEN AS A
STRONG MAN, NOT ONLY TO HIS OWN
CITIZENS, BUT TO CITIZENS OF THE
WORLD.
SO IT'S NOT SURPRISING THAT
DONALD TRUMP WOULD WANT TO DO A
DISPLAY LIKE THIS.
>> CONGRESSMAN BEYER, YOU
REPRESENT VIRGINIA'S EIGHTH
DISTRICT, HOME THE PENTAGON,
YOU'RE JUST ACROSS THE RIVER
FROM WASHINGTON, D.C.
WHAT'S YOUR OBJECTION TO WHAT
THE PRESIDENT HAS PLANNED FOR
THE FOURTH?
>> MELVIN, I HAVE THREE BIG.
FIRST THAT HE'S TAKING SOMETHING
THAT'S ALWAYS BEEN BIPARTISAN, I
GREW UP IN THE CITY AND MY DAD
WOULD LOAD THE SIX KIDS OF US,
TAKE US DOWN TO THE MALL WITH
THE BLANKET AND THE PICNIC
BASKET AND NOW IT'S TURNED INTO
THIS MAJOR PARTISAN THING.
I'M STILL ENCOURAGING OUR FOLKS
DO BECAUSE I DON'T WANT IT TO BE
DIVISIVE.
I OBJECT TO THE MILITARIZATION.
WHEN I THINK OF TROOPS WALKING
DOWN THE MIDDLE, I'M THINKING
RED SQUARE NORTH KOREA, EGYPT,
NOT THE UNITED STATES WHERE
WE'RE GOING TO SPEND 3-QUARTERS
OF A TRILLION DOLLARS ON OUR
MILITARY.
EVERYONE KNOWS WE'RE THE MOST
POWERFUL MILITARY IN THE WORLD.
>> YOU ALSO, AS I UNDERSTAND IT,
YOU ARE CALLING FOR THE
PRESIDENT TO PERSONALLY
REIMBURSE TAXPAYERS FOR ANY
INFRASTRUCTURE DAMAGE CAUSED BY
MILITARY HARDWARE BROUGHT IN FOR
THE CELEBRATION.
I THINK YOU AND I BOTH KNOW THE
PRESIDENT'S NOT GOING TO DO
THAT, BUT WHAT IS YOUR GOAL WITH
THAT DEMAND?
>> WELL, HE'S FAMOUS FOR NOT
PAYING HIS BILLS.
I THINK HE STILL OWES THE
DISTRICT $53 MILLION UNREIMBURSE
FROM THE INAUGURATION.
IT'S JUST TO MAKE THE POINT THAT
WHEN YOU TAKE THESE VERY
WEIGHTY, 60-TON ABRAMS TANKS AND
PUT THEM NEXT TO THE LINCOLN
MEMORIAL, WHO KNOWS WHAT IT'S
DOING TO D.C. ROADS.
THERE'S SOME CONCERN FROM THE
PARK SERVICE THAT THE BASEMENTS
UNDER THE MEMORIAL MAY NOT BE
ABLE TO HOLD THIS UP.
IT'S JUST AT A TIME WHEN THE
PARK SERVICE HAS AN 11 OR
$12 BILLION INFRASTRUCTURE
BACKLOG TO BE REDIRECTING FUNDS
FOR HIS VANITY SHOW, JUST
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
>> CONGRESSMAN BEYER, I
APPRECIATE YOUR TIME, SIR.
THANK YOU.
TO BE CLEAR, YOU'RE GOING TO GO?
YOU'RE GOING TO BE THERE?
>> I'M GOING TO GO ON THE
EASTERN SHORE WITH MY FAMILY SO,
NO, I WILL NOT BE THERE.
>> YOU'LL BE WATCHING ON
TELEVISION.
>> NOT OUT OF PROTEST.
PREVIOUSLY PLANNED.
>> BUT YOU'RE ENCOURAGING YOUR
CONSTITUENTS TO GO.
>> YEAH.
ONLY BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, HE'S THE
MOST DIVISIVE PRESIDENT WE'VE
HAD.
BUT ONE OF OUR GREAT CHALLENGES
IS WE LIVE IN A DIVIDED COUNTRY
AND WE NEED TO DO OUR BEST TO
HEAL.
AND THEY DON'T HAVE TO LISTEN TO
HIS SPEECH BUT THEY SHOULD ENJOY
THE FIREWORKS.
>> WHY ENCOURAGE THEM TO GO IF
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO GO?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, IF I WERE IN
TOWN I PROBABLY WOULD BUT MY
WIFE AND KIDS ARE ALREADY ON THE
EASTERN SHORE.
>> GOT IT.
CONGRESSMAN, THANK YOU FOR YOUR
TIME.
JENNIFER, I WANT TO CALL YOUR
ATTENTION TO THIS SURVEY.
THERE'S A SURVEY OF AMERICAN
PRIDE.
IT'S FROM GALLOP.
AND ACCORDING TO THE SURVEY, 45%
OF FOLKS WHO ARE POLLED ARE
PROUD TO BE AN AMERICAN.
THAT'S THE SECOND STRAIGHT YEAR
OF THE SUB50 RATINGS THAT.
PERCENTAGE HAS BEEN WEAKENING IN
RECENT YEARS.
TO WHAT DO YOU ATTRIBUTE THE
DROP.
>> FIRST OF ALL I WANT BE GOING
TO THE MALL AND IT WON'T BE IN
PROTEST.
GOOD FOR THE CONGRESSMAN, HE'S A
BETTER PERSON THAN I.
I THINK PEOPLE ARE DEEPLY
DISTURBED WITH WHAT THIS
PRESIDENT HAS BEEN DOING TO OUR
DEMOCRATIC INSTITUTIONS.
TO THE RULE OF LAW, TO THE
CELEBRATION OF POWERS, HIS
DISRESPECT FOR THE FIRST
AMENDMENT CALLING THE PRESS THE
ENEMY OF THE PEOPLE.
FOR BETTER OR WORSE, THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
EMBODIES THE COUNTRY TO SOME
DEGREE.
HE IS BOTH THE HEAD OF STATE AND
THE HEAD OF GOVERNMENT.
AND WHEN PEOPLE LOOK AT DONALD
TRUMP AS THEIR REPRESENTATIVE ON
THE WORLD STAGE, THEY ARE NOT
PROUD OF HIM.
THEY FIND HIM TACKY, THEY FIND
HIM CRUDE, RACIST, HOMOPHOBIC,
MISOGYNISTIC, YOU CAN GO DOWN
THE LIST.
AND I THINK THAT DEEPLY WORRIES
PEOPLE.
I THINK YOU SEE THIS IN THE
DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL RACE
WHERE THESE PEOPLE ARE
ESSENTIALLY RUNNING ON A
PLATFORM TO RESTORE AMERICAN
VALUES OF DECENCY,
INCLUSIVENESS, GENEROSITY,
COMMUNITY.
BECAUSE WE HAVEN'T GOTTEN THAT
FROM THIS PRESIDENT.
HE'S NOTORIOUSLY AWFUL ON THESE
MOMENTS WHEN YOU LOOK TO THE
PRESIDENT TO HEAL, TO BRING US
TOGETHER, HE'S THE ANTIUNITER.
AND THIS IS JUST ONE MORE
DISPLAY.
IT'S ALSO REALLY A CONTEMPT FOR
GOVERNMENT.
THIS IS THE MOTHER OF ALL HATCH
ACT VIOLATIONS.
THIS IS USING THE TAXPAYERS'
MONEY, THE TAXPAYERS' PROPERTY
REALLY FOR HIS OWN VANITY.
AND WHETHER IT'S A LEGAL
VIOLATION OR NOT, IT IS SO
UNSEEMLY.
AND I WOULD JUST ADD ONE FINAL
THING.
SEEING TANKS ON THE MALL HAS THE
APPEARANCE THAT WASHINGTON IS AN
OCCUPIED CITY.
WE PUT TANKS ON THE STREET WHEN
THERE'S A CIVIL UPRISING, WHEN
THERE'S A CALAMITY OF SOME TYPE.
THERE IS NOT.
AND DONALD TRUMP DOESN'T GET
THAT THIS IS NOT A SYMBOL OF
PRIDE OR OF AMERICA, BUT THIS
THAT IS A DEEPLY DISTURBING SIGN
THAT HE IS POLITICIZING THE
MILITARY AND MILL TAR MILITARYI
COUNTRY.
>> ARE WE AT A POINT WHERE WE
CAN'T SEPARATE OUR PATRIOTISM
FROM THE PRESIDENT?
>> I THINK THOSE PLUNGING
NUMBERS AROUND AMERICAN PRIDE
ARE TOTALLY REFLECTIVE OF THE
FACT THAT WE'RE IN A POLARIZED
NATION.
WE HAVE A PRESIDENT WHO IS
LEADING THROUGH DIVISION AND
DISCORD.
YOU'RE SEEING THAT NUMBER
INCREASE SLIGHTLY AMONG
REPUBLICANS AND PLUNGE AMONG
DEMOCRATS.
WE'RE A VERY DIVIDED SOCIETY.
BUT I WORRY TOO WHAT RONALD
REAGAN WARNED ABOUT IN HIS
FAREWELL ADDRESS.
HE TALKED ABOUT THE ERADICATION
OF THE AMERICAN MEMORY AND EAT
RECOGNITION OF THE AMERICAN
SPIRIT.
BY WHICH HE MEANT WE ARE NOT --
WE ARE NOT STUDYING CIVICS AND
HISTORY IN OUR SCHOOLS ANYMORE.
WE'RE LOOKING ONLY AT THE MOMENT
RIGHT NOW IN AMERICAN HISTORY.
AND WHAT DONALD TRUMP MEANS TO
AMERICA, NOT THE LARGER AMERICAN
STORY.
I THINK IF AMERICANS, MORE
AMERICANS WERE TO UNDERSTOOD
MORE ABOUT CIVICS AND AMERICAN
HISTORY, THEY WOULD HAVE PRIDE
IN OUR NATION KNOWING THAT
SOMETIMES WE GO THROUGH GOOD
TIMES AND SOMETIMES WE GO
THROUGH BAD TIMES, BUT WE ARE A
STRONG AND RESILIENT NATION
ULTIMATELY.
>> ON THIS EVE OF THE FOURTH OF
JULY, THAT SEEMS AN APPROPRIATE
SPOT TO END IT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR THAT,
MARK.
THANK YOU, ASHLEY, THANK YOU
JENNIFER, AND THANK YOU MONICA.
DO APPRECIATE YOUR REPORTING.
>>> DANGEROUS CONDITIONS.
CHILDREN LAYING ON TOP OF EACH
OTHER.
CELLS PACKED AT FIVE TIMES THEIR
CAPACITY.
NEW IMAGES BEING RELEASED AS
PART OF A GOVERNMENT WATCHDOG
REPORT ON CONDITIONS INSIDE
THOSE MIGRANT DETENTION
FACILITIES.
IT'S TRIGGERING MORE OUTRAGE
ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND ON THE
CAMPAIGN TRAIL.
I'LL TALK ABOUT IT WITH ONE OF
THE DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CONTENDERS WASHINGTON GOVERNOR
JAY INSLEE WILL JOIN ME ON THE
OTHER SIDE OF THIS BREAK.
LATER IN THIS HOUR, ANOTHER
CONTEND ARE, OHIO CONGRESSMAN
TIM RYAN WILL ALSO JOIN ME.
HE'S GOT A WARNING FOR HIS PARTY
ON THE ISSUE OF IMMIGRATION AND
WHAT IT COULD MEAN FOR THE
PRESIDENTIAL RACE.
IT COULD MEAE
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
What do all these people
have in common, LiMu?
[ guttural grunt ]
Exactly. Nothing!
They're completely
different people.
That's why they
make customized
car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need.
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done it again, LiMu.
[ LiMu grunts ]
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
Tell him we're flexible.
Don't worry. My Dutch is OK.
Just OK?
(in Dutch)
Tell him we need this merger.
It's happening..!
Just OK is not OK.
Especially when it comes to
your network.
AT&T is America's best wireless
network
according to America's biggest
test.
Now with 5G Evolution.
The First Step to 5G.
More for your thing. That's our
thing.
>>> A DISTURBING NEW REPORT FROM
THE OFFICE OF THE INSPECTOR
GENERAL HIGHLIGHTS THE
CONDITIONS MIGRANTS ARE FACING
AT THE SOUTHERN BORDER.
IT INCLUDES IMAGES OF PEOPLE AT
A RIO GRANDE VALLEY DETENTION
CENTER CRAMMED INTO HOLDING
CELLS, SLEEPING ON CONCRETE
FLOORS.
ONE SENIOR MANAGER AT THAT
FACILITY CALLS THE SITUATION A,
QUOTE, TICKING TIME BOMB.
OFFICIALS FOUND ADULTS AND
CHILDREN LIVING WITH LIMITED
ACCESS TO SHOWERS.
AND ACCORDING TO THAT REPORT,
QUOTE, AT ONE FACILITY SOME
SINGLE ADULTS WERE HELD IN
STANDING ROOM ONLY CONDITIONS
FOR A WEEK AND AT ANOTHER SOME
SINGLE ADULTS WERE HELD FOR MORE
THAN A MONTH IN OVERCROWDED
CELLS.
JOINING ME NOW LIVE FROM
SEATTLE, WASHINGTON, GOVERNOR
AND POLITICAL -- EXCUSE ME,
DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATE JAY INSLEE.
GOVERNOR, THANK YOU FOR YOUR
TIME.
AS PRESIDENT, WHAT WOULD YOU DO
ABOUT THESE DETENTION
FACILITIES?
HOW WOULD THEY CHANGE?
>> WE WOULD SHOP THE GROSS
INHUMANITY.
YOU NEED TO UNDERSTAND THE DEPTH
AND DEPRAVITY OF DONALD TRUMP.
THESE CONDITIONS ARE AN
INTENTIONAL ACTION BY HIM.
HE HAS MADE IT VERY CLEAR THAT
HE WANTS TO MAKE PEOPLE AFRAID
AND HE LIKES THESE INHUMANE
CONDITIONS BECAUSE IT IS PART OF
HIS INTENTION TO FAN THE FLAME
OF DISCORD AROUND HIM
AGGREGATION.
IMMIGRATION.
AND INSTEAD OF TRYING TO ADDRESS
THE ROOT CAUSES OF THIS
IMMIGRATION PROBLEM TO KEEP
PEOPLE WHERE THEY LIVE AND NOT
FORCE THEM TO COME NORTH, HE HAS
DECIDED TO UTILIZE INHUMANE
CONDITIONS AS A TOOL OF HIS
GROSS CRUELTY.
WE NEED TO UNDERSTAND HOW DEEP
THIS DEPRAVITY IS.
SO WE NEED TO HAVE BOTH
ADDITIONAL CAPACITY FOR PEOPLE,
BUT WE NEED TO GO BACK WHAT
WE'VE DONE FOR 50 YEARS AS A
JUDGE ORDERED YESTERDAY IN
SEATTLE, TO ALLOW PEOPLE TO BE
RELEASED ON BOND IN THE
APPROPRIATE CIRCUMSTANCES
WHEREAS MUCH AS 80 OR 90% OF
PEOPLE DO RETURN FOR THEIR
IMMIGRATION HEARINGS.
WE'VE DONE THAT FOR 50 YEARS IN
AMERICA.
HE HAS DEPARTED FROM AMERICAN
TRADITION.
WE NEED TO GO BACK TO THAT.
>> ON LAST NIGHT, FELLOW
DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATE FORMER
HOUSING SECRETARY JULIAN CASTRO
APPEARED ON RACHEL MADDOW AND HE
LAID OUT HIS IMMIGRATION PLAN.
LISTEN HAVE SOME I'M GOING TO
OFFER A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
VISION ON WHAT WE SHOULD DO ON
IMMIGRATION TO MAKE SURE THAT WE
HAVE AN IMMIGRATION SYSTEM
THAT'S FIXED, THAT WORKS WITH
BORDER SECURITY, BUT THAT NEVER
TREATS PEOPLE LIKE THIS AGAIN.
I BELIEVE ONE CENTERPIECE OF
THAT IS REPEALING SECTION 1325
OF THE IMMIGRATION NATIONAL ALT
ACT SO THAT NOT ONLY THIS
PRESIDENT, BUT FUTURE PRESIDENTS
CAN'T EVER USE THAT LAW TO
INCARCERATE PARENTS AND SEPARATE
THEM FROM THEIR LITTLE CHILDREN.
>> DO YOU AGREE WITH HIS STANCE
THAT CROSSING THE BORDER
ILLEGALLY SHOULD BE
CRIMINALIZED?
>> WE SHOULD NOT USE CRIMINAL
STATUTES TO SEPARATE CHILDREN
FROM THEIR PARENTS, PERIOD.
AND IF THAT'S BEING USED FOR
THAT PURPOSE, IT SHOULD NOT BE
USED FOR THAT PURPOSE.
AND IS NOT REQUIRED.
LOOK, WE HAVE LOTS OF CIVIL
SYSTEMS TO BE ABLE TO PREVENT
ILLEGAL ENTRY INTO THE UNITED
STATES.
AND TO USE DONALD TRUMP'S
SEPARATION OF CHILDREN FROM
PARENTS, WHICH HE HAS DONE
INTENTIONALLY, SHOULD NOT BE
ALLOWED THROUGH CRIMINAL
STATUTES IN THE UNITED STATES.
AND I WANT TO REPEAT, LOOK, FOR
50 YEARS WE'VE HAD A SYSTEM OF
BEING ABLE TO ALLOW PEOPLE TO
HAVE A HEARING ON ASYLUM WITHOUT
SEPARATING CHILDREN FROM THEIR
PARENTS.
WE NEED TO RESTORE THAT BASIC
AMERICAN VALUE.
>> I WANT TO HIGHLIGHT SOMETHING
FROM THE NEW "WASHINGTON POST,"
ABC NEWS POLL THAT WAS TAKEN
SINCE LAST WEEKS NBC DEBATE.
29% OF DEMOCRATIC VOTERS SAY
HEALTHCARE IS ONE OF THE MOST
IMPORTANT ISSUES THEY'RE GOING
TO BE VOTING ON.
TOP OF THE LIST, IN FACT.
YOU HAVE RELIED HEAVILY ON
CLIMATE CHANGE.
YOU'VE DRILLED DOWN ON CLIMATE
CHANGE.
WHAT DO YOU OFFER VOTERS WHO ARE
LOOKING FOR SOMEONE TO TACKLE
OUR NATION'S HEALTHCARE ISSUES?
>> WELL, WE HAVE DONE SO MUCH IN
OUR STATE SUCCESSFULLY, NOT JUST
IN CLIMATE -- ADDRESSING THE
CLIMATE CRISIS.
WE'VE ADOPTED THE VERY FIRST
PUBLIC HEALTH OPTION IN THE
UNITED STATES.
WE'RE PROUD OF THAT.
I'M THE FIRST GOVERNOR TO
ACTUALLY WORK WITH OUR COMMUNITY
TO PASS THOSE BILLS.
BUT WE'VE DONE SO MUCH ON OUR
OTHER ISSUES TO HELP FAMILIES
HEALTH.
HEALTH IS NOT JUST THE
HEALTHCARE SYSTEM, YOU'VE GOT TO
HAVE A FAMILY WAGE.
THAT'S WHY I'M PROUD TO SAY
WE'VE ADOPTED WHILE I'M GOVERNOR
THE HIGHEST MINIMUM WAGE IN THE
UNITED STATES.
YOU HAVE TO BE ABLE TO TAKE CARE
OF YOUR FAMILY WHEN THEY'RE
SICK.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE THE MOST
ROBUST MEDICAL FAMILY LEAVE IN
THE UNITED STATES.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE A DECENT WAGE
IN GENERAL, THAT'S WHY I'M PROUD
OF WE'VE WON THE HIGHEST
EDUCATOR COMPENSATION INCREASE
FOR OUR TEACHERS AND EDUCATORS
IN THE UNITED STATES.
WE HAVE WRAPAROUND SERVICES OF
BEING ABLE TO BUILD A MID-MIDDLE
CLASS.
THAT'S HOW YOU REALLY HAVE
HEALTH.
BUT I DO WANT TO COME BACK TO
THIS ISSUE.
LOOK, THIS IS A HEALTH ISSUE OF
THIS CLIMATE CRISIS.
IT'S INCREASING LYME DISEASE,
IT'S RESPIRATORY DISTRESS, IT'S
AN EPIDEMIC OF AS ASTHMA.
THE CLIMATE CRISIS IS A HEALTH
ISSUE AND I'M OFFERING A UNIQUE
EMPHASIS TON.
I AM THE CANDIDATE AND SO FAR
THE ONLY CANDIDATE WHO SAID THIS
WILL BE THE NUMBER ONE PRIORITY
OF THE UNITED STATES.
IT'S A HEALTH ISSUE, IT'S AN
ECONOMIC ISSUE ALL ROLLED IN
ONE.
>> IT'S YOUR CENTRAL MESSAGE.
>>> YOU BET.
>> THE LATEST MSNBC POLL SHOWS
YOUR MOVEMENT OVER THE LAST FOUR
MONTHS, IT SHOWS IN MARCH,
APRIL, AND JUNE YOU WERE
REGISTERING AT ABOUT 1%.
IN THE MOST RECENT PERCENT
YOU'RE NOT AT AN AS SPER RISK.
ASTERISK?
IS IT THAT MESSAGE OR IS IT
ABOUT THE MESS SEN JER.
>> WHERE WE'RE CLINTON AND
CARTER WERE WHEN THEY STARTED.
WE'RE STILL INTRODUCING
OURSELVES TO THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE.
LESS THAN A THIRD OF THE PEOPLE
COULD PICK ME OUT OF A LINEUP IN
THE IS A START.
WE'VE HAD SOME CONFIDENCE SINCE
THE LAST DEBATE.
WE HAD A SURGE OF SUPPORT.
WE HAD THE LARGEST NUMBER OF
DONORS IN 24 HOURS SINCE I
STARTED.
WE HAD THE LARGEST NUMBER OF NEW
DONORS.
AND WE ENCOURAGE FOLKS TO GO TO
JNZ.COM IF THEY WANT TO SEE THE
CLIMATE CRISIS TO REMAIN A
CENTRAL FOCUS OF THE DEBATE.
>> YOU'RE TALKING NUMBERS HERE,
YOU'VE GOT SOME FUNDRAISING
NUMBERS FOR US?
>> YEAH.
THEY'RE GOING UP.
I DON'T HAVE A TOTAL NUMBER FOR
YOU.
I HAVEN'T TOTALED THEM FOR THE
QUARTER.
BUT WE DID HAVE THE BEST DAY,
THE BEST TWO DAYS THAT WE'VE HAD
DURING THE CAMPAIGN AFTER THE
LAST DEBATE.
AND I THINK IT IS BECAUSE PEOPLE
WANT TO SEE THE CLIMATE CRISIS
FRONT AND CENTER.
>> YESTERDAY SENATOR SANDERS PUT
OUT HIS NUMBERS, HE WAS AROUND
24 MILLION.
PETE PUT OUT HIS NUMBERS AROUND
ARE YOU AT 24 MILLION.
>> NO.
BY THE WAY, I WAS HONORED THE
OTHER DAY, SOMEONE EVALUATED OUR
RESPECTIVE CLIMATE PLANS AND
OURS WAS HELD TO BE NUMBER ONE,
I'M PROUD OF THAT.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT'S NECESSARY
IS FOR OUR NATION TO ADDRESS
SOMETHING THAT'S BURNING DOWN
OUR TOWNS AND PLANNED TOING OUR
FIELDS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> AND IF PEOPLE WANT TO SEE
THAT, THEY CAN GO TO JNZ.COM.
>> GOVERNOR INSLEE, THANK YOU.
>> YOU BET.
>>> TOP TIER SHUFFLE.
HOW THE LATEST POST NBC NEWS
DEBATE POLL SHAKING UP SOME OF
THE TOP CONTENDERS AS JOE BIDEN
REMAINS AT THE TOP SPOT.
WE'LL GO LIVE TO IOWA WHERE A
NUMBER OF CANDIDATES ARE HITTING
THE GROUND FOR THE HOLIDAY.
WE'LL CATCH UP WITH OUR ROAD
WARRIORS IN THE HAWKEYE STATE IN
THE IS A LIVE LOOK AT DES
MOINES.
E STATE IN
THE IS A LIVE LOOK AT DES
MOINES
♪
Corey is living with
metastatic breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking IBRANCE
with an aromatase inhibitor,
which is for postmenopausal
women
or for men with HR+ / HER2-
metastatic breast cancer
as the first hormonal
based therapy.
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease progression
versus letrozole.
Patients taking IBRANCE
can develop
low white blood cell counts,
which may cause
serious infections
that can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE, tell your
doctor if you have fever,
chills, or other signs
of infection,
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects include
low red blood cell
and low platelet counts,
infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth,
abnormalities in
liver blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash, and
loss of appetite.
Corey calls it her new normal
because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor
about IBRANCE.
The #1 prescribed FDA-approved
oral combination treatment
for HR+/HER2- MBC.
This is the story of John Smith.
Not this John Smith.
Or this John Smith.
Or any of the other
hundreds of John Smiths
that are Humana Medicare
Advantage members.
No, it's this John Smith.
Who we paired with a Humana
team member to help address
his own specific health needs.
At Humana, we take a personal
approach to your health,
to provide care that's just
as unique as you are.
No matter what your name is.
♪
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
What do all these people
have in common, LiMu?
No matter what your name is.
[ guttural grunt ]
Exactly. Nothing!
They're completely
different people.
That's why they
make customized
car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need.
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done it again, LiMu.
[ LiMu grunts ]
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
>>> RIGHT NOW A LOT OF THE 2020
DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES ARE SWARMING IOWA
PREPARING FOR A LONG HOLIDAY
WEEKEND.
THERE'S A LOOK AT THEM THERE.
NEW POLL FROM THE "WASHINGTON
POST" AND ABC NEWS SHEDS SOME
LIGHT ON HOW THEY ARE STACKING
UP AT THIS EARLY POINT IN THE
RACE.
AND THE LATEST POLL SINCE THE
NBC NEWS DEBATE, JOE BIDEN'S
LEAD OVER HIS CLOSEST COMPETITOR
SHRANK TO JUST SIX POINT.
BERNIE SANDERS HOLDING ON TO THE
SECOND SPOT IN THE POLL.
ELIZABETH WARREN HOLDING STEADY
AT 11%.
BIGGEST JUMP, SENATOR KAMALA
HARRIS ALSO AT 11%.
BUT THIS POLL IS UNIQUE BECAUSE
IT ALSO ASKS -- IT ASKS VOTERS
FOR A SECOND CHOICE.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT WHETHER ONE OF
THESE CANDIDATES IS SOMEONE'S
FIRST OR SECOND CHOICE, JOE
BIDEN HAS THE SUPPORT OF HALF
THE PRIMARY VOTERS AND THAT'S
WITH MORE THAN 20 PEOPLE IN THIS
RACE.
SANDERS HITS 40%, ELIZABETH
WARREN AS YOU CAN SEE THERE,
25%.
KAMALA HARRIS RIGHT THERE AS
WELL, 24%.
WE HAVE TWO ROAD WARRIORS
COVERING TWO OF THE BIGGEST
MOVERS IN ALL OF THESE POLLS
RIGHT NOW.
MIKE IS COVERING THE BIDEN
CAMPAIGN, IS HE IN CEDAR RAPIDS,
IOWA.
VAUGHN HILLYARD COVERING THE
HARRIS CAMPAIGN IN DES MOINES,
IOWA.
MIKE, I'LL START WITH YOU IF THE
THIS IS BIDEN'S FIRST CAMPAIGN
RALLY SINCE THOSE DEBATES.
WHAT'S THE PLAN?
>> WELL, CRAIG, THERE'S NO DOUBT
THAT A LOT HAS CHANGED FOR THE
BIDEN CAMPAIGN AHEAD OF WHAT IS
HIS THIRD TRIP TO IOWA SINCE
ANNOUNCING HIS CANDIDACY IN
APRIL.
HE WAS BEHIND ME HERE IN CEDAR
RAPIDS ON THAT FIRST TRIP IN
APRIL SAYING AT THE TIME THAT NO
ONE WAS GOING TO WORK HARDER
THAN HIM TO WIN THE SUCH IOWA
VOTERS.
THAT SECOND TRIP TO IOWA, YOU'LL
REMEMBER HE WAS HERE AT THE SAME
TIME AS PRESIDENT PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
GAVE BIDEN AND OPPORTUNITY TO
FRAME THAT GENERAL ELECTION
MATCHUP, OF COURSE ELECTABILITY
BEING ONE OF THE STRONGEST
ARGUMENTS THAT HE HAS SO FAR.
BUT AS I SAID, THERE'S NO DOUBT
WHEN YOU TALK TO BIDEN ADVISERS
THEY FEEL THE GAME HAS CHANGED.
GAME ON AS ONE ADVISER SAID.
YOU LOOK AT SOME OF THESE POLLS
THAT SHOW HIM SLIPPING AFTER
THAT SHAKY DEBATE PERFORMANCE.
SENIOR BIDEN CAMPAIGN ADVISER
TELLS ME WE'RE NO MORE WORRIED
ABOUT THESE LATEST POLLS THAT
SHOW A LITTLE BIT OF A DIP THAN
THEY WERE OVERCONFIDENT BASED ON
THE INITIAL POLLS THAT SHOWED
HIM WITH A STRONG LEAD.
BUT WE ARE SEEING HIM RECOGNIZE
THAT HE CAN'T JUST STAY ABOVE
THE FRAY IN TERMS OF THE RUN THE
IN THE DEMOCRATIC PRIMARY.
WHAT WILL BE INTERESTING, WE'RE
GOING TO SEE HIM CAMPAIGNING ON
THE FOURTH OF JULY TOMORROW IN
INDEPENDENCE, IOWA, AT THE SAME
TIME AS BETO O'ROURKE.
ANOTHER ONE OF HIS CONTENDERS.
ALSO, CRAIG, TOMORROW NIGHT JOE
BIDEN WILL ALSO BE ATTENDING AN
IOWA/CUBS GAME WITH BETO AROARK.
WHICH MEANS I GET PAID TO ATTEND
A BASEBALL GAME.
>> GOOD POINT.
MR. HILLYARD, HOW ARE THEY GOING
TO CAPITALIZE ON THIS?
>> SHE'LL BE JUST NEXT DOOR IN
WEST DES MOINES THIS AFTERNOON
AND THEN SHE'LL BE GOING FROM
IOWA TO TO NEW ORLEANS AND IN
SOUTH CAROLINA NEXT WEEK.
ESSENTIALLY SHE'S NOT GOING TO
LET UP OFF THE GAS.
SHE'S GOING TO GO FORWARD.
AND THIS IS PART OF THE
CAMPAIGN'S EFFORT TO CONTINUE TO
SHOW THE CONTRAST OF WHAT KAMALA
HARRIS CAN BRING TO THE CAMPAIGN
TRAIL.
SHE PLANS TO GO FULL ON.
THEY NOW HAVE 65 STAFFERS HERE
ON THE GROUND IN IOWA.
AND AS MIKE JUST MENTIONED, THE
DEBATE WAS A WAKEUP CALL FOR THE
BIDEN CAMPAIGN, THAT HE COULDN'T
STAY ABOVE THE FRAY.
BECAUSE WHAT LAST WEEK SHOWED IS
THIS IS GOING TO BE A DEMOCRATIC
PRIMARY IN WHICH CANDIDATES WILL
SHOW CONTRAST BETWEEN THEM.
KAMALA HARRIS NOT ONLY ON ISSUES
OF RACE AND BUSING, BUT ALSO ON
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION'S
DEPORTATION POLICIES.
I WANT TO PLAY FOR YOU A LITTLE
BIT OF SOUND.
THIS WAS ACTUALLY FROM JUST OVER
A WEEK AGO WHEN KAMALA HARRIS
WAS OVER IN SOUTH CAROLINA.
I THINK IT'S VERY PERTINENT TO
WHAT WE SHOULD EXPECT TO HEAR
FROM THE CALIFORNIA SENATOR
TODAY AND IN THE WEEKS AHEAD.
>> WE NEED SOMEBODY WHO AS
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
UNDERSTANDS THE NEED TO REBUILD
THE PARTY.
WHO UNDERSTANDS THE NEED TO GIVE
THE RESOURCES AND THE SUPPORT TO
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE ON THE GROUND
EVERY DAY DOING THE HARD WORK.
WE CAN'T JUST HELICOPTER IN
HERE.
WE HAVE TO SUPPORT THE PEOPLE
WHO ARE ON THE GROUND WHO KNOW
THE COMMUNITY.
>> KAMALA HARRIS IN THAT DEBATE
MADE HERSELF VULNERABLE TO
FOLKS, TO VOTERS WHO SAY THEY
ARE ANXIOUS ABOUT DEMOCRATS
ATTACK ONE ANOTHER.
BUT WHAT SHE DID AT THE SAME
TIME AND WHAT THE POLLS ARE
INDICATING, SHE SEPARATED
HERSELF AS A WILLINGNESS TO
PAINT CONTRAST BETWEEN HER AND
OTHERS.
AND AS YOU JUST HEARD FROM HER
THERE IN SOUTH CAROLINA, WHAT WE
SHOULD EXPECT TO HEAR FROM HER
HERE IN IOWA IS THAT SHE IS
MAINTAINING SHE IS THE CANDIDATE
THAT'S LOOKING FORWARD AND WILL
OUTWORK THE REST OF THE FIELD.
CRAIG.
>> ALL RIGHT.
VAUGHN HILLYARD THERE IN DES
MOINES.
THANK YOU.
AND MIKE, THANK YOU AS WELL,
SIR.
WILL THEY OR WON'T THEY?
A NEW TWEET FROM PRESIDENT TRUMP
JUST MOMENTS AGO APPEARS TO
CONTRADICT HIS OWN
ADMINISTRATION ON A CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION ON THE CENSUS.
WE'RE GOING TO DIG INTO THAT.
IT'S A DEVELOPING STORY.
>>> ALSO THE NEWEST ROUND OF
POST NBC NEWS DEBATE POLLS
SUGGEST THAT THAT SOME
CANDIDATES MIGHT BE IN MORE
TROUBLE WHEN IT COMES TO
REACHING THE DEBATE STAGE.
ONE OF THOSE CONTENDERS HITTING
THE GROUND IN IOWA THIS WEEK.
CONGRESSMAN TIM RYAN WILL JOIN
US AHEAD.
S WEEK
CONGRESSMAN TIM RYAN WILL JOIN
US AHEAD
♪ I want it that way...♪
I can't believe it.
That Karl brought his
karaoke machine?
♪ Ain't nothing but
a heartache... ♪
No, I can't believe how easy
it was to save hundreds of
dollars on my car
insurance with GEICO.
♪ I never wanna
hear you say... ♪
No, Kevin...
no, Kevin!
Believe it!
GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
or more on car insurance.
GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
Alice loves the smell
of Gain so much,
she wished it came in
a fabric softener too.
[throat clears]
Say hello to your fairy
godmother, Alice.
Oh and look they got Gain scent
beads and dryer sheets too!
It all comes down
to a single defining moment...
...when a plan stops being a
plan and gets set into motion.
Today's Merrill
can help you get there
with the people, tools,
and personalized advice
to help turn your ambitions
into action.
What would you like
the power to do?
No matter what I wore, I worried
someone might see
my bladder leak underwear.
So, I switched.
To Always Discreet Boutique.
Its shape-hugging threads smooth
out the back.
So it fits better than Depend.
And no one notices.
Always Discreet.
I'M ALEX TREBEK
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85
AND LOOKING
TO BUY LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE, AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 65 AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH FOR YOU, TOO.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE NUMBER ONE MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
IT HAS AN AFFORDABLE RATE
STARTING AT $9.95 A MONTH.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE IS GUARANTEED,
AND THIS PLAN HAS A GUARANTEED
LIFETIME RATE LOCK,
SO YOUR RATE CAN NEVER GO UP
FOR ANY REASON.
AND WITH THIS PLAN,
YOU CAN PICK YOUR PAYMENT DATE,
SO YOU CAN TIME
YOUR PREMIUM DUE DATE
TO WORK WITH YOUR BUDGET.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
AND YOU'LL ALSO GET
THIS FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
AND IT'S YOURS JUST FOR CALLING.
SO CALL NOW.
>>> MOMENTS AGO PRESIDENT TRUMP
TOOK TO TWITTER TO SAY THAT HE
WILL DEFY HIS OWN JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT AND THE COURTS ON THE
CENSUS.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS THAT THE
CENSUS WILL HAVE A CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION.
NBC WHITE HOUSE CORRESPONDENT
KELLY O'DONNELL IS HERE TO TRY
TO CLEAR THIS UP.
HEY, KELLY, JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
SAYS NO, PRESIDENT SAYS YES.
WHAT DO WE KNOW ABOUT WHAT'S
HAPPENING.
>> Reporter: WELL, IT'S A LITTLE
MORE COMPLICATED AND WHAT THIS
REALLY GETS DOWN TO IS THE
PRESIDENT DOES NOT LIKE THIS
DECISION.
AND THIS, OF COURSE, IS THE
PRESIDENT WHO ARGUES FORCEFULLY
THAT ASKING THOSE WHO REPLY TO
THE 2020 CENSUS IF THEY ARE
AMERICAN CITIZENS IS AN
IMPORTANT PIECE OF DATA ALONG
WITH ALL THE OTHER THINGS THAT A
CENSUS COLLECTS.
WHAT WE LEARNED LATE TUESDAY,
YESTERDAY, WAS THAT THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE AND THE
DEPARTMENT OF COMMERCE WERE
GOING FORWARD WITH PRINTING OF
THE 2020 QUESTIONNAIRE WITHOUT
THE CITIZENSHIP QUESTION.
NOW IS THERE SOME GRAY AREA
HERE?
YOU CAN KEEP A LEGAL CHALLENGE
GOING WHICH THE PRESIDENT IS
ARGUING FOR HERE.
AND AT THE SAME TIME TAKE THE
PRAGMATIC STEP OF PRINTING THE
UP IN CENSUS AND DOING IT
LAWFULLY WITHOUT THAT
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION NOW BECAUSE
OF THE ENORMITY OF THE TASK OF
DOING THE 2020 CENSUS.
SO WHAT WE NEED SOME
CLARIFICATION ON IS, IS THE
PRESIDENT DIRECTLY DEFYING THIS
PLAN TO PRINT OR IS HE ARGUING
FOR CONTINUING THE LEGAL CASE?
WHICH AT THE PUSHED IT BACK TO
THE LOWER COURT SAYING THE
REASONS GIFG GIVEN BISECT WILBUR
ROSS WERE NOT SUFFICIENT TO
ADDING THIS QUESTION AND IT WAS
AN OPPORTUNITY OPPORTUNITY FOR
THE ADMINISTRATION TO KEEP
LITIGATING.
BUT THEY'RE RUNNING UP AGAINST A
TIME DEADLINE, BECAUSE THE
CONSTITUTION, NOT JUST ANY
ORDINARY LAW, BUT THE
CONSTITUTION REQUIRES THAT A
CENSUS BE TAKEN EVERY TEN YEARS.
SO WE'RE UP AGAINST THAT
DEADLINE.
IS IT PRAGMATISM MEETS POLITICS?
IS IT A PRESIDENT THAT'S BEEN
ACTIVE TON TWITTER TODAY PUSHING
BACK?
THIS DECISION BY THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT AND CONGRESS THAT WE
LEARNED LATE YESTERDAY FOLLOWED
WITHIN 24 HOURS OF THE PRESIDENT
ARGUING PRETTY FORCEFULLY THAT
HE WANTED TO KEEP FIGHTING THIS.
SO THE PRESIDENT HAS SORT OF
BEEN PUSHED BACK ON HIS HEELS
WITH THIS.
HE'S CALLING IT FAKE NEWS.
WE HAVE OFFICIALS IN BOTH
DEPARTMENTS WHO TOLD US THE PLAN
IS TO GO FORWARD WITH THE
PRINTING.
SO IS HE ADVOCATING FOR THE
COURT CASE TO GO ON?
IS THIS JUST SORT OF A POLITICAL
MESSAGE FROM THE PRESIDENT?
TO OUR UNDERSTANDING, THE CENSUS
QUESTION -- THE CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION IS NOT IN THE UP IN
PRINTING THAT WILL BE ORDERED
FAIRLY SHORTLY.
CRAIG.
>> KELLY O'DONNELL FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE.
THANK YOU.
>>> I'M JOINED NOW BY SENIOR
CORRESPONDENT FOR NPR BOSTON AND
MSNBC CONTRIBUTOR KIMBERLY
ATKINS.
ALSO WITH ME, ASSISTANT
PROFESSOR OF PUBLIC POLICY AT
HARVARD UNIVERSITY.
LEAH, THANK YOU LADIE, BOTH FOR
BEING WITH ME.
APPARENTLY THE PRINTER IS
INSTRUCTED TO START THE PROCESS.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE, LEAH?
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF DIFFERENT
ISSUES THAT ARE GOING ON HERE.
FIRST, WE SEE AGAIN, THAT THE
PRESIDENT IS COMPLETELY AT ODDS
WITH OTHER FACTIONS OR OTHER
AGENCIES OR DIVISIONS,
DEPARTMENTS WITHIN HIS OWN
ADMINISTRATION.
SO IT RAISES THE QUESTION, YOU
KNOW, WHO'S IN CHARGE HERE?
WHO'S RUNNING THE SHOW?
THE OTHER THING TOO THAT I THINK
IS IMPORTANT TO KEEP IN MIND IS
THAT THE PRESIDENT IS
ESSENTIALLY SAYING, AND THIS MAY
BE SABER RAD RATTLING AND
SHOWING A HARD POLITICAL MESSAGE
THAT HE MEANS BUSINESS,TOR MAY
BE SERIOUS.
BUT HE'S SPECIALLY SAYING I'M
GOING TO GO AGAINST THIS AND GO
AGAINST THE COURT'S RULING AND
MY OWN JUST DEPARTMENT AND I'M
GOING TO ENSURE THAT THAT
QUESTION FINDS ITS WAY ON THERE.
SO HE'S PROMISING TO REALLY
UPHOLD THE, YOU KNOW, THIS
QUESTION ABOUT CITIZENSHIP AND
CHANGE THE CENSUS.
NOW, CAN HE DO THAT?
IT'S NOT EXACTLY CLEAR.
HOW WOULD HE DO THAT.
BUT HE'S ESSENTIALLY PROMISING
DO THAT.
AND THAT IS CAUSE FOR CONCERN.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
KIMBERLY, I THINK FOR FOLKS WHO
ARE WATCHING AND WHO ARE
LISTENING ON SIRIUS SATELLITE
RADIO WHO PERHAPS HAVEN'T BEEN
FOLLOWING THIS STORY AS CLOSELY,
MAYBE WE SHOULD REMIND THEM WHY
IS IT THAT THIS PRESIDENT FINDS
THE CITIZENSHIP QUESTION ITSELF,
WHY DOES HE WANT THIS TO BE A
PART OF THIS CENSUS SO VERY
BADLY?
>> WELL, IT'S A COUPLE OF
POLITICAL REASONS FOR THIS,
CRAIG.
ONE IS THAT WHEN THE CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION IS ON THE CENSUS, THERE
IS RESEARCH THAT WOULD SAY THAT
IT WOULD ACTUALLY WORK TO
SUPPRESS PARTICIPATION IN THE
CENSUS AND GET AN UNDERCOUNT
PARTICULARLY NOT JUST OF PEOPLE
WHO ARE IMMIGRANTS, BUT EVEN
CITIZENS WHO ARE RELATED TO
IMMIGRANTS HAVE FOLKS WHO ARE OF
MIXED IMMIGRATION STATUS WITHIN
THEIR HOUSEHOLD.
THERE WILL BE A FEAR THAT
PARTICIPATING IN THE CENSUS
COULD GET THEM IN TROUBLE.
WE HAVE SEEN THROUGHOUT
DOCUMENTATION AND THE LITIGATION
OVER THE CENSUS THERE ARE SOME
FOLKS WHO KNOW THAT THAT WOULD
HURT DEMOCRATS IN AN ELECTION.
I MEAN, THE CENSUS DECIDES A LOT
OF THINGS FROM CONGRESSIONAL
DISTRICTS TO FEDERAL FUNDING,
BUT IT WILL HAVE AN IMPACT ON
THE ELECTION COULD A DEPRESSED
TURNOUT AND DEPRESS THE STRENGTH
OF THE DEMOCRATIC DISTRICTS.
SO THERE'S A POLITICAL INCENTIVE
HERE.
I'VE TALKED TO STATE OFFICIALS
WHO HAVE SAID EVEN WITH THE
CENSUS QUESTION NOT ON THE
CENSUS, THERE HAS BEEN SO MUCH
DISCUSSION, SO MANY DIVISIVENESS
OVER THIS ISSUE THAT THEY ARE
STILL FEARING THAT THERE WILL BE
AN UNDERCOUNT.
AND THAT WILL BE PROBLEMATIC FOR
THE STATES WHO DEPEND ON THE
CENSUS FOR THEIR FEDERAL
FUNDING.
>> ALSO IN THE NEWS TODAY, OF
COURSE, THESE TROUBLING IMAGES
THAT WE ARE GETTING THANKS TO
THAT WATCHDOG GROUP OF THE
MIGRANT DETENTION CENTERS FROM
INSIDE THESE MIGRANT DETENTION
CENTERS.
I ASKED PRESIDENTIAL HOPEFUL JAY
INSLEE JUST A FEW MOMENTS AGO
ABOUT HIS PLAN FOR IMMIGRATION.
AND WE ALSO TALKED ABOUT
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S STRATEGY ON
IMMIGRATION.
LEAH, KIMBERLY, THIS IS WHAT HE
SAID.
>> HE HAS MADE IT VERY CLEAR
THAT HE WANTS TO MAKE PEOPLE
AFRAID AND HE LIKES THESE
INHUMANE CONDITIONS BECAUSE IT
IS PART OF HIS INTENTION TO FAN
THE FLAME OF DISCORD AROUND
IMMIGRATION.
AND INSTEAD OF UNITING US TO
FIND A COMPREHENSIVE SOLUTION,
INSTEAD OF TRYING TO ADDRESS THE
ROOT CAUSES OF THIS IMMIGRATION
PROBLEM, TO KEEP PEOPLE WHERE
THEY LIVE AND NOT FORCE THEM TO
COME NORTH, HE HAS DECIDED TO
UTILIZE INHUMANE CONDITIONS AS A
TOOL OF HIS GROSS CRUELTY.
>> LEAH, IS WHAT WE'RE SEEING,
IS IT THE PRESIDENT'S STRATEGY
OR IS IT THE RESULT OF A FAILED
STRATEGY?
>> SO, YOU KNOW, THE ANSWER IS
YES TO BOTH.
I THINK ONE OF THE THINGS THAT
HAS EMERGED OR THE PAST COUPLE
YEARS IS THAT THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN VERY,
VERY DIRECT IN SOME WAYS, IN
SOME WAYS NOT TO DIRECT, BUT HAS
BEEN PRETTY DIRECT ABOUT SAYING
THAT THEIR SEPARATION POLL VIS
ARE THEIR POLICIES AROUND THE
BORDER, THESE DETENTION CENTER
POLICIES HAVE BEEN MADE TO
DISSUADE PEOPLE FROM COME
TOGETHER BORDER.
AND IT'S NOT BEEN SUCCESSFUL.
AND WE'VE SEEN AN EXPLOSION IN
THE TREATMENT, THESE CENTERS,
AND THEN KIND OF POOR
CONDITIONS.
WE'VE SEEN THE ADMINISTRATION
ARGUING IN FAVOR OF POOR
CONDITIONS.
NOW, THE BIGGER THING I THINK,
AND THIS IS GOING TO BE A
QUESTION FOR MOST DEMOCRATIC
CANDIDATES MOVING INTO -- INTO
PRIMARY DEBATES AND INTO THE
GENERAL ELECTION IS WELL, WHAT
ARE YOU GOING TO DO ABOUT IT?
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO TO FIX
IT?
WHAT IS THE POLICY ON
IMMIGRATION, ASYLUM SEEKERS, AND
REFUGEE CENTERS, AND THEN THE
CONDITIONS THESE PEOPLE ARE
FACING.
BECAUSE RIGHT NOW IT'S
UNSUSTAINABLE.
AS A POLITICAL STRATEGY PERHAPS
IT'S WORKING FOR PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S SUPPORTERS, BUT FOR THE
REST OF THE COUNTRY IT
ABSOLUTELY IS NOT WORKING.
>> KIMBERLY, LET'S TALK POLITICS
FOR JUST A SECOND HERE.
AND THEN MAYOR PETE
SPECIFICALLY.
WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT HIS
FUNDRAISING NUMBERS DURING OUR
LAST SEGMENT.
BERNIE SANDERS AS WELL PUT UP
ABOUT 24 MILLION.
ACTUALLY BERNIE SANDERS
TRANSFERRED ABOUT 6 MILLION, HE
RAISED ROUGHLY 18.
BUT MAYOR PETE RAISED CLOSE TO
$25 MILLION.
THAT'S PRETTY IMPRESSIVE FOR A
SECOND QUARTER.
BUT --
>> YEAH.
>> YOU LOOK AT HIS POLLING AND
THE TWO DON'T SEEM TO MAKE
SENSE.
WHY -- WHY IS HE NOT POLLING
BETTER IF HE IS RAISING SO MUCH
MONEY?
>> WELL, A FEW REASONS.
I'VE BEEN TALKING TO PEOPLE WHO
ARE RAISING MONEY FOR MAYOR PETE
AS HE TRAVELS TO PLACES,
INCLUDING MASSACHUSETTS THIS
UPCOMING WEEKEND.
AND THEY SAY THAT ON THE GROUND
HE IS RESONATING WITH FOLKS.
THEY'RE DOING A COMBINATION OF
THESE BIG-DOLLAR FUNDRAISERS
THAT FOLKS LIKE ELIZABETH WARREN
AND BERNIE SANDERS HAVE CHOSEN
NOT TO DO.
BUT ALSO DOING THE
SMALLER-DOLLAR DONATIONS IN
ORDER TO ENERGIZE YOUNGER
PEOPLE, REALLY ALLOW PEOPLE TO
GET TO KNOW HIM.
AND IT HAS BEEN LITERALLY PAYING
OFF.
NOW ONE THING THAT RAISING THIS
MONEY WILL DO WILL ALLOW HIM TO
STAY IN THE RACE LONGER THAN
SOME OF THE OTHER CANDIDATES AND
GIVE HIM MORE OF AN OPPORTUNITY
TO BUILD HIS PROFILE, GET OUT
WITH ADS, AND RAISE HIS PROFILE.
I THINK A LOT OF PEOPLE JUST
DON'T KNOW WHO HE IS OR WHAT
HE'S ABOUT YET.
AND THAT COULD HAPPEN.
BUT, ON THE OTHER HAND, HE'S HAD
A PARTICULARLY DIFFICULT TIME
RESONATING WITH VOTERS OF COLOR.
WE KNOW THAT FOR DEMOCRATS THAT
SAY CRUCIAL, CRUCIAL BLOCK.
HE HAD THE ISSUE WITH THE POLICE
SHOOTING.
>> YEAH.
>> IN SOUTH BEND.
AND SO THAT IS A BIG -- THAT'S A
BIG OBSTACLE THAT HE'S GOING TO
HAVE TO OVERCOME.
BUT AT LEAST FOR NOW HE HAS THE
FUNDS TO STAY IN IT.
>> KIMBERLY ATKINS, LEAH, ENJOY
THE HOLIDAY, LADIES.
THANK YOU OR YOUR TIME.
>> THANK YOU.
>>>ESE HE'S BEEN EXTREMELY VOCAL
ABOUT WINNING BACK THOSE VOTERS
THAT SWUNG TO TRUMP.
CONGRESSMAN TIM RYAN SOUNDING
OFF ON THE EFFECT THE
IMMIGRATION DEBATE COULD HAVE ON
THE RACE.
CONGRESSMAN RYAN JOINS ME AFTER
THE BREAK.
E RACE
CONGRESSMAN RYAN JOINS ME AFTER
THE BREAK.
Nothing feels like connecting
with the people that matter.
Holiday Inn.
Holiday Inn Express.
We're there.
So you can be too.
I have one kid in each branch
of the military,
but I'm command central.
It's so important to us
that Verizon
is supporting military families.
When I have a child deployed,
having a reliable network
means everything.
So, when I get a video chat,
and I get to see their face,
it's the best thing
in the world.
And I've earned every one
of these gray hairs.
Military moms, we serve too.
(VO)
The network more people rely on,
gives you more.
Like military plans with
a special price on Unlimited,
$100 per line, and big savings
on our best phones
when you switch.
That's Verizon.
Think all premium fuels
are the same?
New Shell V-Power NiTRO+ Premium
Gasoline is engineered
with four levels of defense
against
gunk, wear, corrosion and
friction.
That helps keep your engine
running like new.
So, maybe it's time to unthink
what you think
you think about premium fuel.
Shell V-Power NiTRO+ Premium
Gasoline...
It's Fuel For Thought.
MAKING THE OVERCROWDED AND
DANGEROUS CONDITIONS REVEALED IN
THESE MIGRANT DETENTION
FACILITIES A NATIONAL FOCAL
POINT.
I'M JOINED NOW BY OHIO
DEMOCRATIC CONGRESSMAN AND
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE TIM RYAN.
CONGRESSMAN, WE HAVE ALL SEEN
THESE PICTURES NOW AND WE'VE
HEARD SOME OF THE HEARTBREAKING
STORIES OF THE MIGRANTS FROM THE
DETENTION FACILITIES.
A NUMBER OF THE OTHER CANDIDATES
HAVE VISITED AND RELEASED SOME
DETAILED PLANS ON HOW TO DEAL
WITH THEM.
I DON'T BELIEVE YOU'VE DONE
EITHER JUST YET.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
WHAT WOULD YOU DO WITH THESE
DETENTION FACILITIES,
SPECIFICALLY FACILITIES THAT ARE
PRIVATELY OPERATED?
GO AHEAD.
>> YEAH, WE SHOULD NOT BE
LOCKING THESE PEOPLE UP IN THE
WAY WE'RE DOING IT.
CRAIG, IT'S ATROCIOUS.
I THINK IT GOES AGAINST OUR
VALUES.
I THINK WE NEED TO MAKE SURE --
I WISH THE PRESIDENT WOULD ASK
DOCTORS AND NURSES TO GO
IMMEDIATELY TO THE BORDER AND
START HELPING ADMINISTER SOME
CARE TO THESE PEOPLE.
JAMMING THEM IN THESE
FACILITIES, I MEAN THIS IS
STUNNING TO THINK THAT THIS IS
THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA.
AND IT'S CONTRIBUTING TO THE
LEVEL OF ANXIETY THAT WE HAVE
ACROSS OUR SOCIETY TODAY, CRAIG.
I MEAN, EVERYONE IS TELLING US
THINGS ARE GOING REALLY GOOD,
BUT YET EVERYBODY FEELS REALLY
BAD.
AND THIS ANXIETY, JUST WATCHING
THESE THINGS HAPPEN, LET ALONE
IF YOU'RE IN ANY WAY CONNECTED
TO THESE PEOPLE THAT ARE DOWN
THERE IS JUST HEARTBREAKING.
AND WE'RE THE UNITED STATES.
WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO GO DOWN
THERE AND FIX THIS AND IT
SHOULDN'T TAKE THAT LONG.
>> WHAT WOULD YOU DO ON DAY ONE,
IF ELECTED, ABOUT THIS
SPECIFICALLY?
>> WELL, MAKE SURE EVERYBODY
COMING IN THROUGH THESE
FACILITIES IS TAKEN CARE OF.
BUT THE KEY IS GOING TO BE TO GO
TO CENTRAL AMERICA AND ACTUALLY
STABILIZE THOSE COUNTRIES WHERE
PEOPLE ARE MIGRATING FROM.
THE PRESIDENT IS THE DISTRACTER
IN CHIEF.
HE CAN'T FOCUS FOR MORE THAN
FIVE SECONDS.
THE ISSUE IS IN CENTRAL AMERICA.
I'VE BEEN SAYING THIS NOW FOR
MONTHS.
WE NEED TO GO TO CENTRAL
AMERICA, STABILIZE THOSE
COUNTRIES.
KICK THE GANGS OUT.
WE DON'T EVEN HAVE AN AMBASSADOR
IN HONDURAS RIGHT NOW.
THE PRESIDENT IS CUTTING THE
STATE DEPARTMENT FUNDING THAT
WOULD HELP US REPAIR WHAT IS
HAPPENING DOWN THERE.
THAT'S THE HEART OF THE PROBLEM.
THAT'S WHERE PEOPLE ARE COMING
FROM.
AND IF WE WANT TO END THE CRISIS
AT THE BORDER, WE NEED TO GO
DEAL WITH THE HEART OF THE
MATTER.
>> THE CANDIDATES OVER THE
HOLIDAY WEEKEND HERE, YOU ARE IN
IOWA.
YOU'RE IN IOWA RIGHT NOW.
WOULD LOO.
THERE'S A NEW POLL OF IOWA
VOTERS FROM AFTER NBC'S DEBATE
LAST WEEK.
THE THE POLL IS JUST OUT.
THREE OF THOSE WHO PARTICIPATED
IN THE DEBATES, NEW YORK MAYOR
BILL de BLASIO, OHIO
REPRESENTATIVE TIM RYAN AND
CALIFORNIA REPRESENTATIVE ERIC
SWALWELL FAILED TO ATTRACT A
SINGER SUPPORTER.
THAT'S OF 500 PEOPLE IN IOWA WHO
WERE SURVEYED, CONGRESSMAN.
DO YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES TO
STAY IN THIS RACE?
>> NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
I MEAN, LITERALLY OUR PHONE HAS
BEEN RINGING OFF THE HOOK SINCE
THE DEBATE.
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT
WE'RE LEANING TO VICE PRESIDENT
BIDEN WHO ARE CALLING US AND
THEY WANT TO MEET.
WE'VE HAD SOME OF THE BEST
FUNDRAISING DAYS WE'VE HAD SINCE
THE DEBATE.
SO I THINK WE CONNECTED.
CLEARLY THE NATIONAL
CONVERSATION WAS AROUND
SOMETHING DIFFERENT AND I THINK
THESE POLLS AT THIS POINT ARE
ABSOLUTELY MEANINGLESS.
YOU CAN GO BACK AND LOOK AT
WINNERS FROM THE LAST 40 YEARS
AND AT SOME POINT THEY WERE
WHERE I AM NOW.
AND I THINK WE'VE GOT THE
MESSAGE.
WE'RE CONNECTING WITH PEOPLE
AROUND THE STRESS AND ANXIETY
AND FEAR THAT'S FACING THEM.
WHETHER IT'S THE ECONOMIC
ANXIETY, WHETHER IT'S AROUND
HEALTH CARE, WHETHER IT'S AROUND
WHAT WE'RE WATCHING HAPPEN AT
THE BORDER, WHETHER IT'S WHAT'S
HAPPENING IN OUR ENVIRONMENT AND
OUR SOIL AND THE THINGS THAT ARE
HAPPENING ENVIRONMENTALLY.
WE'RE CONNECTING WITH PEOPLE,
CRAIG, AND PEOPLE ARE -- YOU
KNOW, I'M ASKING PEOPLE TO COME
TO TIM RYAN FOR AMERICA.COM, BE
A PART OF THIS CAMPAIGN.
WE JUST RELEASED THE MOST
COMPREHENSIVE EDUCATION AGENDA
TO HELP WITH TRAUMA-BASED CARE
FOR OUR KIDS AND SOCIAL AND
EMOTIONAL LEARNING IN OUR
SCHOOLS AND WRAP-AROUND THERAPY.
SO WE ARE TAKING CARE OF THE BIG
ISSUES IN MY CAMPAIGN AND THAT'S
WHY PEOPLE ARE GETTING ON BOARD.
>> YOU JUST MENTIONED
FUNDRAISING.
HOW MUCH HAVE YOU RAISED IN THE
SECOND QUARTER?
>> WELL, WE DON'T HAVE -- I
DON'T HAVE THE NUMBERS RIGHT
NOW, BUT I WILL TELL YOU THAT
OUR BEST DAYS WERE RIGHT AFTER
THE DEBATE.
AND I WAS REALLY EXCITED ABOUT
THAT AND WE'VE DONE REALLY WELL
INTO JULY.
SO WE'RE MOVING IN THE RIGHT
DIRECTION.
>> $24 MILLION?
>> WE'RE MOVING IN THE RIGHT
DIRECTION.
I'M REALLY PLEASED WITH IT.
>> MAYOR PETE HAS ABOUT $25
MILLION.
BERNIE SANDERS PUT OUT HIS
NUMBERS YESTERDAY AT $24
MILLION.
ARE WE IN THAT NEIGHBORHOOD?
>> WE ARE NOT IN THAT
NEIGHBORHOOD.
I MEAN, HERE'S THE DEAL, CRAIG.
I'M FROM NORTHEAST OHIO.
I'M NOT FROM A BIG CITY.
I'M NOT FROM A BIG STATE.
I DON'T HAVE AN IVY LEAGUE
EDUCATION OR NETWORK THAT I CAN
TAP INTO.
SO WE'RE, YOU KNOW, DOING IT THE
WAY IT HAS TO BE DONE AND THAT'S
GRASS ROOTS, BUILDING THIS BRING
BRICK BY BRICK.
WE'RE MOVING IN THE RIGHT
DIRECTION.
WE JUST STARTED A WHOLE TEACHERS
FOR TIM INITIATIVE AROUND
TEACHERS WHO ARE COMING ON
BOARD.
WE'RE BUILDING THIS THING OUT.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO REMEMBER IT'S
JULY.
BILL CLINTON DIDN'T GET IN THIS
RACE UNTIL OCTOBER.
SO WE ARE WAY AHEAD OF THE GAME
HERE COMPARED TO PAST YEARS.
>> CONGRESSMAN, THANK YOU.
AND ENJOY THE 4th.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> AHEAD IN THE NEXT HOUR, MY
COLLEAGUE ANDREA MITCHELL IS
GOING TO HAVE MORE ON THE
CONTROVERSY SURROUNDING THE
PRESIDENT'S PLANNED 4th OF JULY
EVENT.
(Singsong)
Budget meeting!
Sweet.
If you compare last quarter
to this quarter...
Various: Mmm.
It's no wonder everything
seems a little better
with the creamy taste
of Philly,
made with fresh milk
and real cream.
When you book at Hilton.com, you
get the Price Match Guarantee.
So if you find your
room at a lower rate,
of Philly,
Hilton is like...
We're gonna match that rate
and give you an extra 25% off.
What would travel sites do if
you found a different price?
That's not my problem,
it's your problem.