INJURIES THAT DO GET A CASE AND
DO SAY A POLICEMAN IS WRONG.
ALL POLICEMEN ARE NOT WRONG BUT
ALL OF THEM ARE NOT RIGHT.
WE MUST CORRECT A SYSTEM THAT
SAYS THAT WE WILL DISTINGUISH
CRIME WHETHER THE ACCUSED HAS ON
A BLUE UNIFORM OR BLUE JEANS,
THE LAW MUST BE UP HELD, AND
WEST PALM SENT THAT MESSAGE.
THAT DOES IT FOR ME.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
I'LL SEE YOU BACK HERE TOMORROW
AT 5:00 P.M. EASTERN FOR A NEW
LIVE EDITION OF "POLITICS
NATION", UP NEXT, "DEADLINE
WHITE HOUSE" WITH MY COLLEAGUE
AND FRIEND NICOLE WALLACE.
>>> ALOHA, EVERYONE, IT IS 4:00
IN NEW YORK CITY, I'M JOHN
HEILEMAN, PRESIDENT TRUMP COULD
HAVE SPENT THIS MORNING BASKING
IN THE GLOW OF THE SENTENCE
HANDED DOWN TO HIS FORMER
CAMPAIGN CHAIRMAN, PAUL
MANAFORT, A SENTENCE SO LENIENT
THAT IT GIVES NEW MEANING TO
SOFT ON CRIME.
TRUMP SEES THE CYCLE AND TURNED
IT BACK TO A TOPIC YOU WOULD
THINK HE WOULD WANT TO AVOID,
HIS FORMER FIXER MICHAEL COHEN.
TWEETING ABOUT COHEN'S TESTIMONY
ON CAPITOL HILL NINE DAYS AGO.
HERE'S THAT TWEET.
>> BAD LAWYER AND FRAUDSTER
MICHAEL COHEN, SAID UNDER SWORN
TESTIMONY THAT HE NEVER ASKED
FOR A PARDON.
HIS LAWYERS TOTALLY CONTRADICTED
HIM.
HE LIED.
ADDITIONALLY HE DIRECTLY ASKED
ME FOR A PARDON.
I SAID NO.
HE LIED AGAIN.
HE ALSO BADLY WANTED TO WORK AT
THE WHITE HOUSE.
HE LIED.
NOT ONLY COULD THAT TWEET BE
CONSIDERED AN ACT OF RETALIATION
AGAINST COHEN, A WITNESS WHO IS
ACTIVELY COOPERATING AGAINST
TRUMP, IT'S A BRAND NEW
ADMISSION TRUMP HAD A
CONVERSATION ABOUT A PARDON, AT
A TIME WHEN COHEN WAS LYING ON
TRUMP'S BEHALF.
WE HAVE BEEN HEARING RUMORS
ABOUT PARDON TALKS BETWEEN
WITNESSES BUT THIS IS THE FIRST
TIME WE HAVE BEEN HEARING THAT
TRUMP MAY HAVE BEEN PERSONALLY
INVOLVED IN THOSE DISCUSSIONS.
NEEDLESS TO SAY, TRUMP'S TWEET
HAS OPENED HIM UP TO MORE
QUESTIONS ABOUT WHETHER HE
DANGLED PARDONS IN FRONT OF MANY
OTHER OF THE CONVICTED FELONS
WHO WERE IN HIS INNER CIRCLE.
THAT'S A TOPIC WE KNOW IS
UNDERSCRUTINY BY THREE SEPARATE
INVESTIGATIVE BODIES.
ROBERT MUELLER COUNSEL, THE
SOUTHERN DISTRICT OF NEW YORK
AND THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE.
AS IF THAT WASN'T ENOUGH
POTENTIAL PERIL ON THE PARDON
FRONT, TRUMP ALSO JUST TODAY
APPEARED TO LEAVE THE DOOR AJAR
TO GUESS WHAT, A PARDON FOR PAUL
MANAFORT.
>> I FEEL VERY BADLY FOR PAUL
I THINK IT'S BEEN A VERY VERY
TOUGH TIME FOR HIM, BUT IF YOU
NOTICE, BOTH HIS LAWYER, A
HIGHLY RESPECTED MAN, AND A VERY
HIGHLY RESPECTED JUDGE, THE
JUDGE SAID THERE WAS NO
COLLUSION WITH RUSSIA.
THIS HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
COLLUSION.
THERE WAS NO COLLUSION.
IT'S A COLLUSION HOAX, IT'S A
COLLUSION WITCH HUNT.
THE ONLY ONE DISCUSSING IT IS
YOU.
I HAVEN'T DISCUSSED IT.
>> THAT'S NEW.
A COLLUSION WITCH HOAX.
THAT IS WHERE WE START TODAY
WITH SOME OF OUR FAVORITE
REPORTERS AND FRIENDS, PHIL
RUCKER, MATTHEW MILLER, FORMER
CHIEF SPOKESPERSON FOR THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT, FORMER
DEPUTY ASSISTANT ATTORNEY
GENERAL AND U.S. ATTORNEY, HARRY
LITMAN, AND NBC NEWS POLITICAL
REPORTER, GUYS GREAT TO SEE YOU.
WISH YOU WERE HERE AT THE DESK.
I WANT TO START WITH YOU HARRY
LITMAN AND ASK YOU THIS
QUESTION.
IT SOMETIMES TO ME THAT DONALD
TRUMP WITH HIS TWEET MAY HAVE
OPENED HIMSELF UP TO, HARD TO
BELIEVE, ADDITIONAL NEW LEGAL
EXPOSURE.
AM I RIGHT OR AM I WRONG?
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
HE IS THE WORST CLIENT OF ALL
TIME.
EVERY TIME HE OPENS HIS MOUTH,
IT'S MORE PROBLEMS FOR HIM.
HE'S HERE.
A WITNESS, IT MAKES ALL THE
SENSE IN THE WORLD AND THE SDNY
CONGRESS MIGHT ASK, REALLY, MR.
PRESIDENT, WHERE WERE YOU, WHAT
DID YOU SAY TO MICHAEL COHEN IS
THIS THE ONLY TIME YOU SPOKE
ABOUT PARDONS.
BECAUSE OF HIS POSITION AS
PRESIDENT HE'S BEEN ABLE TO
ELUDE ASKING QUESTIONS.
PERHAPS HE DOES IT HERE.
YOU HAVE TO IMAGINE THAT NED
FLOOD AND ALL TRUMP LAWYERS ARE
CRINGING ONCE AGAIN TO HEAR HIM
BASICALLY ADMITTING, YES, WE HAD
THIS CONVERSATION, COME AND ASK
ME ABOUT IT.
>> MATT MILLER, I ASK YOU, I
THINK, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE MORE OF
A SCHOLAR OF PRESIDENTIAL AND
LEGAL MATTERS THAN I AM BUT IT
SEEMS TO ME IT'S POSSIBLE THAT
DONALD TRUMP IN TWO PLUS YEARS
IN THE WHITE HOUSE HAS MENTIONED
THE WORD PARDON IN PUBLIC MORE
THAN ALL OF OUR PREVIOUS
PRESIDENTS COMBINED.
WHAT IS THAT ABOUT?
>> I THINK IT'S VERY CLEARLY
ABOUT SENDING A MESSAGE TO
WITNESSES AND DEFENDANTS AND
OTHERS WHO MIGHT -- WHO ARE
FACING THIS DIFFICULT CHOICE
ABOUT WHETHER TO COOPERATE WITH
INVESTIGATORS AND TELL
EVERYTHING THEY KNOW,
POTENTIALLY IMPLICATING THE
PRESIDENT OR IMPLICATING THE
PRESIDENT'S FAMILY OR OTHER
PEOPLE CLOSE TO THE PRESIDENT OR
WHETHER TO SIT AND NOT TALK TO
THEM AND HOLD OUT UNTIL THE END
OF A TRIAL OR A GUILTY PLEA
KNOWING THAT AT SOME DAY, THE
PRESIDENT MIGHT BE THERE FOR
THEM.
I THINK THAT'S WHY HE HAS SENT
THAT MESSAGE IN PRIVATE AS YOU
ALLUDED TO.
IT'S BEEN REPORTED THAT HIS
PREVIOUS ATTORNEY JOHN DOWD HAD
CONVERSATIONS WITH THE ATTORNEYS
FOR MIKE FLYNN AND PAUL
MANAFORT.
WHY MAYBE HE HAD THIS DISCUSSION
WITH MICHAEL COHEN.
IT'S WHY HE SAID IT SO MUCH.
HIS LINE ABOUT WE ARE THE ONLY
ONES TALKING ABOUT IS NOT TRUE.
HE HAS TWEETED ABOUT IT, BROUGHT
IT UP IN OTHER INTERVIEWS, IT'S
BEEN A CONSTANT TOPIC OF
CONVERSATION OFTENTIMES BROUGHT
UP BY HIM AS IT WAS IN THE TWEET
TODAY.
>> HEIDI, THERE'S REPORTING,
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" TALKS ABOUT
HOW TRUMP'S LAWYERS HAVE OFFERED
PARDONS OR DISCUSSED PARDONS
WITH PAUL MANAFORT AND MICHAEL
FLYNN PREVIOUSLY.
I MEAN, AGAIN, THIS PARDON TALK
IS JUST, I MEAN, IT'S BEEN A
CONSTANT FEATURE, AND OBVIOUSLY
ON SOME LEVEL IT'S BECAUSE OF
THE FACT THERE'S MORE LEGAL
JEOPARDY AND PEOPLE AROUND TRUMP
WHO HAVE BEEN IN LEGAL TROUBLE
THAN ANY PRESIDENT IN HISTORY.
AS WE GET A SENSE OF HOW MUCH
THIS HAS BECOME A FABRIC OF THE
DISCUSSION, ESPECIALLY IN
RELATION TO SOME OF THE PEOPLE
THAT ARE CONVICTED FELONS OR
SOON TO BE CONVICTED FELONS,
WHAT DO WE MAKE OF ALL OF THAT,
AND WHERE THAT DISCUSSION IS
HEADED AND WHAT WE SHOULD MAKE
OF IT?
>> WELL, I WOULD SAY THAT THE
BACKDROP TO ALL OF THIS, IF I
TAKE YOU BACK TO THE VERY
BEGINNING OF THE SPECULATION AS
TO WHAT WOULD HAPPEN TO PAUL
MANAFORT WAS THAT THERE WERE
ONLY TWO POSSIBLE EXPLANATIONS
TO EXPLAIN HIS BEHAVIOR AND WHY
HE WASN'T BEING MORE
COOPERATIVE.
EVEN TO THIS DAY, THE SPECIAL
COUNSEL'S OFFICE SAYS THAT HE
WAS NOT OFFERING VERY MUCH
INFORMATION SO THE TWO POSSIBLE
EXPLANATIONS WOULD BE THAT, ONE,
HE WAS EXPECTING A PARDON, OR
TWO, WHATEVER WOULD HAPPEN TO
HIM, IF HE ACTUALLY DID SING, IF
HE ACTUALLY DID TALK BECAUSE OF
HIS CONNECTIONS TO THE RUSSIANS
WOULD BE WORSE THAN WHAT IS
GOING TO HAPPEN TO HIM IN TERMS
OF HIS SENTENCING.
SO THE PARDONS AND THE PROSPECT
OF PARDONS HAS BEEN PART OF THE
FABRIC FROM THE VERY BEGINNING
AND NOT JUST BECAUSE OF PAUL
MANAFORT BUT BECAUSE OF THE
MESSAGE IT MIGHT SEND TO MANY
OTHER POTENTIAL COOPERATING
WITNESSES IN TERMS OF MICHAEL
FLYNN.
THE INVESTIGATIONS NOW ARE GOING
INTO A PHASE, THOUGH, JOHN,
WHERE THEY'RE GOING TO BE
GETTING INFORMATION OFF THE HILL
FROM MANY OTHER PEOPLE WHO ARE
COOPERATING AND I JUST MET THIS
MORNING WITH SOME AIDES FROM ONE
OF THOSE COMMITTEES AND THEY SAY
THAT ACTUALLY THEY'RE GETTING A
LOT OF COOPERATION FROM
WITNESSES WHO HAVE ALREADY
PROVIDED THAT INFORMATION TO
MUELLER.
SO EVEN IF WE DON'T SEE THAT
INFORMATION IN TERMS OF A FINAL
REPORT FROM MUELLER, IT IS BEING
EXTRACTED NOW BY THESE
DEMOCRATIC OVERSIGHT COMMITTEES
ON THE HILL.
>> SO PHIL, I WANT TO ASK YOU, I
WANT TO FOCUS ON ONE PARTICULAR
THING ABOUT THIS COHEN TWEET,
WHICH IS THE KIND OF OUT OF THE
BLUENESS OF IT, AND YOU KNOW, IT
WAS NINE DAYS AGO THAT MICHAEL
COHEN TESTIFIED ON CAPITOL HILL,
AND OBVIOUSLY HE HAS BEEN BACK
AND COHEN'S NEVER REALLY OUT OF
THE NEWS, BUT WHAT IS IT YOU
THINK ON THE BASIS OF YOUR
REPORTING AND INTUITION THAT
WOULD CAUSE TRUMP ON THIS
PARTICULAR MORNING TO DECIDE TO
GO AFTER, TO RAISED MICHAEL
COHEN SPECTER AGAIN.
>> YEAH, JOHN, WELL, THE REASONS
I THINK IS ALL WEEK WE HAVE SEEN
VARIOUS ALLEGATIONS PRESENTED BY
COHEN'S LAWYERS, AND
EXPLANATIONS BY TRUMP'S LAWYERS,
INCLUDING RUDY GIULIANI IN THE
MEDIA ABOUT THE EXTENT OF THESE
PARDON CONVERSATIONS, WHAT
EXACTLY THEY WERE.
EARLIER THIS WEEK, MICHAEL COHEN
WAS ON CAPITOL HILL IN CLOSED
DOOR TESTIMONY TALKING ABOUT
THESE CONVERSATIONS.
ACCORDING TO OUR REPORTING, HE
WAS TELLING CONGRESSIONAL
INVESTIGATORS THAT HE HAD HAD
NUMEROUS CONVERSATIONS ABOUT A
PARDON THAT HAD BEEN DANGLED
BEFORE HIM BY TRUMP'S LEGAL
REPRESENTATIVES INCLUDING RUDY
GIULIANI, AND SO IT'S BEEN IN
THE ETHER THOUGH WE'RE REMOVED
FROM COHEN'S TESTIMONY, AND THE
PRESIDENT FELT LIKE HE WANTED TO
WEIGH IN.
WHAT THE PANEL HAS UNDERSCORED
WHAT TRUMP TWEETED IS VERY
DIFFERENT THAN WHAT COHEN IS
ALLEGING ON CAPITOL HILL.
TRUMP IS TWEETING THAT HE
HIMSELF HAD A CONVERSATION WITH
COHEN ABOUT A PARDON AND COHEN
ASKED HIM FOR A PARDON AND HE
SAID NO.
NOW, THIS IS A PRESIDENT WHO HAS
NEVER BEEN KNOWN TO BE
ESPECIALLY PRECISE IN HIS
RECOLLECTIONS OR HIS NARRATION
OF EVENTS, SO I DON'T KNOW IF
THAT WAS THE TRUTH, BUT IT WAS
AN EXTRAORDINARY TWEET.
>> NO, AND HARRY, IT DOES RAISE
THIS ISSUE, RIGHT, WHICH IS,
AGAIN, THE PERSONAL NATURE THAT
PHIL ALLUDES TO, THE NOTION THAT
TRUMP HIMSELF WAS INVOLVED IN
THESE DISCUSSIONS.
IT SEEMS TO ME THAT ONE OF THE
THINGS YOU WOULD DO.
YOU SAID HE'S THE WORST CLIENT
IN THE WORLD BUT IF YOU WANTED
TO MAINTAIN A CERTAIN AMOUNT OF
PLAUSIBLE DENIABILITY, YOU COULD
SAY I DON'T KNOW WHAT MY LAWYERS
ARE DOING, THEY MAY HAVE TALKED
ABOUT PARDONS WITH THESE FOLKS,
I PERSONALLY THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES WOULD NEVER
GET INVOLVED IN THIS.
TRUMP TODAY SEEMS TO HAVE
STRIPPED AWAY ANY PLAUSIBLE
DENIABILITY ON HIS PART.
IT MAKES ABSOLUTELY NO SENSE WHY
THE PRESIDENT WOULD WANT TO
INSERT HIMSELF PERSONALLY IN
THIS DISCUSSION.
>> YEAH, 100%, WHY TODAY, YOU
KNOW, THAT PATH LIES MADNESS, HE
GETS AN ITCH, HE HAS TO SCRATCH
IT.
IT'S 3:00 A.M., AND HE JUST DOES
BUT RIGHT, IT'S NOT IN HIS
SELF-INTEREST EXCEPT OF COURSE
WE HAVE BEEN PILLARING HIM AS A
CLIENT, DESERVEDLY, BUT, YOU
KNOW WE'RE IN THE POLITICAL
REALM.
DOES PUTTING IT OUT THERE NOW
FOR SOME REASON GIVE A LITTLE
JOLT TO THE BASE THAT HE FELT HE
NEEDED AND IS THAT THE METHOD IN
HIS MADNESS POSSIBLY.
>> I WANT TO FOCUS A LITTLE BIT
ON MANAFORT HERE YOU GUYS, THERE
HAS BEEN A TON OF DISCUSSION
SINCE THE SENTENCE WAS HANDED
DOWN LAST NIGHT ABOUT HOW
LENIENT AND FLAGRANT IT WAS AND
THE TWO TIERS OF JUSTICE.
RUDY GIULIANI HAD A QUOTE, I
FEEL TERRIBLE ABOUT THE WAY
MANAFORT HAS BEEN TREATED.
I THINK IT'S NOT AMERICAN TO
KEEP A MAN IN SOLITARY
CONFINEMENT, TRY TO CRACK HIM.
HE'S NOT A TERRORIST.
HE'S NOT AN ORGANIZED CRIMINAL.
HE'S A WHITE COLLAR CRIMINAL.
NOTHING TO ME SCREAMS MORE THE
TWO AMERICAS HERE OR THE TWO
TIERED NATURE OF AMERICAN
JUSTICE THAT WE COULD HAVE A
CONVERSATION IN WHICH SOMEONE
WHO IS GUILTY OF THE KIND OF
CRIMES THAT PAUL MANAFORT WAS
CONVICTED OF TO SAY IT'S NOT A
SERIOUS CRIME.
HE'S NOT A TERRORIST AND
THEREFORE HE'S A JAYWALKER, WHAT
DO YOU MAKE OF THE SENTENCE
ITSELF AND CAST YOUR MIND
FORWARD TO NEXT WEEK WHEN A NEW
JUDGE IS GOING TO BE LOOKING AT
PAUL MANAFORT'S OTHER CRIMES AND
HAS THE POSSIBILITY OF ADDING
TEN MORE YEARS ON TO HIS
CUMULATIVE SENTENCE.
>> FIRST TIME YOU SAY ABOUT
ROUGE, KIND OF TRITE WHAT A
HYPOCRITE HE'S BECOME, BUT IT'S
IMPORTANT HERE BECAUSE ONE OF
THE WAYS RUDY GIULIANI MADE HIS
NAME AS A PROSECUTOR WAS
PROSECUTING PEOPLE FOR WHITE
COLLAR CRIMES, INSIDER TRADING
AND OTHER CASES ON WALL STREET.
THAT'S WHAT MADE HIM FAMOUS,
WALKING INTO WALL STREET TRADING
FLOORS WITH HANDCUFFS.
THEY ARE SERIOUS CRIMES, AND THE
ONLY PEOPLE IN THE COUNTRY WHO
SEEM TO THINK PAUL MANAFORT WAS
TREATED TO HARSHLY, NOT TOO
LENIENTLY ARE THE PRESIDENT AND
HIS LEGAL TEAM.
I THINK THE PROBLEM WITH THIS
SENTENCE, TWO-FOLD, ONE, IF YOU
JUST LOOK AT THE NATURE OF HIS
CRIMES, SETTING ASIDE WHAT
EVERYBODY ELSE GETS, THE NATURE
OF HIS CRIMES, THE SENTENCING
GUIDELINES, THE TEN-YEAR CRIME
SPREE THAT HE EMBARKED ON, AND
THE SERIOUS GUILTY VERDICTS
RETURNED BY THAT JURY ON EIGHT
COUNTS, OBVIOUSLY I THINK HE
SHOULD HAVE BEEN GIVEN A MUCH
MORE SERIOUS, NOT THE FULL 19 TO
24 YEARS, BUT SOMETHING ALONG
10, 12 YEARS WOULD HAVE BEEN
JUSTIFIED BUT THEN WHEN YOU
COMPARE IT TO EVERYONE ELSE, IT
REALLY DOES DRIVE HOME THIS
PROBLEM, WHICH ISN'T NEW, NOT
UNIQUE TO PAUL MANAFORT.
WEALTHY POWERFUL WHITE
DEFENDANTS CONVICTED OF WHITE
COLLAR CRIMES, AREN'T TREATED
THE SAME AS POOR DEFENDANTS,
BLACK AND BROWN DEFENDANTS,
GUILTY OF VIOLENT CRIMES AND
NONVIOLENCE CRIMES LIKE DRUG
DISTRIBUTION.
>> TO FOLLOW UP FURTHER ON WHAT
I ASKED MAT, THE QUESTION OF
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT, MANAFORT IS
OPEN TO THE POTENTIAL OF BEING
PROSECUTED BY NEW YORK STATE IN
ADDITION TO BEING PROSECUTED FOR
THE CRIMES HE HAS BEEN
PROSECUTED FOR AND YOU HAVE AMY
BERMAN JACKSON, THE JUDGE WHO'S
GOING TO RULE ON HIS SENTENCING
NEXT WEEK.
IF YOU'RE JUDGE BERMAN JACKSON,
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT WHAT
JUST HAPPENED, AND DOES IT PLAY
ANY ROLE IN HOW YOU CAN ABOUT
THE SENTENCE THAT YOU DECIDE TO
HAND DOWN NEXT WEEK?
>> YEAH, THAT IS AN INTERESTING
AND TRICKY QUESTION.
MUELLER'S SENTENCING MEMORANDUM
DROPS A FOOTNOTE THAT ANSWERS
THAT QUESTION YES.
POINTS TO A PROVISION IN THE
SENTENCING GUIDELINES AND
SUGGESTS THAT SHE CAN GO UP TO
TEN YEARS BASED ON HIS OVERALL
CONDUCT, IN OTHER WORDS
ADVERTING TO THE EASTERN
DISTRICT OF VIRGINIA CONDUCT.
I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT, THOUGH,
THAT SHE SHE WOULD HAVE TRIED TO
KEEP IT INDEPENDENT, AND WOULD
BE.
SHE'S A TOUGH SENTENCER, BUT
WOULD BE LOOKING AT SOMETHING
LIKE SEVEN OR EIGHT YEARS.
I DO WANT TO POINT OUT, IT WAS
AN EGREGIOUS DEPARTURE, THE
SYSTEM NOT DONE WITH PAUL
MANAFORT AND PROBABLY NEVER WILL
BE.
THERE IS NOT JUST THIS COMING
UP, ALSO AS YOU SAY THE
POSSIBILITY OF NEW YORK, THREE
OTHER STATES, INCLUDING RHODE
ISLAND AND ILLINOIS COULD
POTENTIALLY INDICT HIM, AND I
THINK ARE BEGINNING TO LOOK AT
THAT HARD BECAUSE OF THIS
SENTENCE.
HE'S BY NO MEANS OUT OF THE
WOODS.
>> PHIL, ONE OF THE THINGS THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP SEIZED ON TODAY,
AS THE MOST PREDICTABLE THING IN
THE WORLD, BESIDES THE SUNRISING
IN THE EAST IS THE NOTION THAT
TRUMP WOULD SEIZE ON THE NOTION
THAT THE JUDGE SAID THERE WAS NO
COLLUSION.
IT'S NOT REALLY WHAT THE JUDGE
SAID.
TALK A LITTLE BIT ABOUT THAT.
I KNOW NO COLLUSION IS GOING TO
BE RINGING IN YOUR EARS PROBABLY
UNTIL THE DAY YOU DAY, GIVEN THE
NUMBER OF TIMES TRUMP SAID IT.
TALK ABOUT THE
MISCHARACTERIZATION OF THE
FACTS.
>> IT'S BEEN RINGING IN OUR EARS
FOR A COUPLE OF YEARS NOW.
THAT WAS A GROSS
MISCHARACTERIZATION OF WHAT
JUDGE ELLIS SAID YESTERDAY.
WHAT HE SAID WAS THAT PAUL
MANAFORT WAS IN THAT COURTROOM
FOR CRIMES THAT DO NOT HAVE TO
DO WITH THE INVESTIGATION OF
COLLUSION BETWEEN THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN AND RUSSIA SO THE
MANAFORT CRIMES WERE SEPARATE
FROM THE TRUMP COLLUSION/RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION.
HE DID NOT AT ALL ARRIVE AT A
JUDGMENT ABOUT RUSSIAN COLLUSION
AND DID NOT GIVE THE PRESIDENT A
CLEAN BILL OF HEALTH AS THE
PRESIDENT, YOU KNOW, CLAIMED ON
THE SOUTH LAWN OF THE WHITE
HOUSE TODAY.
>> HEIDI, I WANT TO READ A TWEET
FROM ADAM SCHIFF, THE CHAIRMAN
OF THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE.
THE STATEMENT BY PAUL MANAFORT'S
LAWYER AFTER AN ALREADY LENIENT
SENTENCE REPEATING THE
PRESIDENT'S MANTRA OF NO
COLLUSION WAS NO ACCIDENT.
IT WAS A DELIVERED APPEAL FOR A
PARDON, ONE INJUSTICE MUST NOT
FOLLOW ANOTHER: SO HE'S
BASICALLY SAYING, FIRST OF ALL,
THE JUDGE DIDN'T SAY NO
COLLUSION, THE LAWYER SAID NO
COLLUSION, AND THAT WAS INTENDED
AS AN APPEAL FOR A PARDON.
TALK A LITTLE BIT ABOUT WHAT YOU
THINK ADAM SCHIFF'S GAME IS
HERE, AND HOW THIS ACTION SHOULD
SHIFT TO CAPITOL HILL ON THE
MANAFORT FRONT.
>> RIGHT, SO BASED ON OUR
REPORTING, THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE ACTUALLY IS GETTING A
LOT OF INFORMATION IN
COORDINATION WITH OTHER
COMMITTEES, LIKE THE FINANCIAL
SERVICES COMMITTEE, IF THEY
EVENTUALLY GET TRUMP'S TAX
RETURNS, THEY'LL GET A LOT MORE
INFORMATION FROM THAT.
BUT THEY ARE GOING HARD AT THE
ISSUE OF COLLUSION.
THAT IS EXACTLY WHAT THEY'RE
GOING TO BE EXAMINING, AND
UNLIKE IN THE SENATE COMMITTEE
WHERE YOU DID HAVE SOME, YOU
KNOW, A LITTLE BIT OF A PARTISAN
BREAK DOWN THERE, ON THE HOUSE
SIDE, THERE'S GOING TO BE MANY
MORE WITNESSES NOW COMING IN,
INCLUDING ALLEN WEISSELBERG THAT
THEY'VE ALREADY GOT COOPERATING
AND BASED ON MY REPORTING
SPEAKING WITH JUDICIARY SOURCES
THIS MORNING, THEY ARE BY FUR
-- BIFURCATING AND TAKING IT
SLOW.
THEY DON'T WANT IT TO BE SEEN AS
OVERREACH, GOING AFTER THE
PRESIDENT, WILLY NILLY,
PARTISANLY THERE IS GOING TO BE
AN OBSTRUCTION ELEMENT ON THIS.
AND THE INTENTION, THE COLLUSION
PART OF THIS STILL HAS MANY MORE
CHARACTERS TO PLAY OUT.
TO REPEAT MYSELF FROM THE FIRST
PART, EVEN IF THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION NEVER BECOMES
PUBLIC, THIS WILL ALL ULTIMATELY
BECOME PUBLIC THROUGH
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE.
I THOUGHT IT WAS NOTABLE THAT
FOR INSTANCE, ONE OF THE
CHARACTERS THAT SCHIFF WANTS TO
BRING BEFORE HIS COMMITTEE IS
FELIX SAIDER, VERY CLOSE TO THE
TRUMP FAMILY AND VERY CLOSE TO
THE RUSSIAN MAFIA.
IT'S NOTABLE THAT SCHIFF WANTED
TO BRING HIM INITIALLY IN
PUBLIC, WHICH MEANS THEY HAVE
ALREADY GOT THEIR HANDS ON A LOT
OF INFORMATION THAT THEY WANT TO
BRING TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
>> THAT WAS SCHEDULED FOR NEXT
WEEK AND HAS BEEN DELAYED UNTIL
LATER IN MARCH.
HEIDI, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
YOUR TIME.
HARRY LITMAN FOR YOUR GOOD LOOKS
AND GENIUS WHEN YOU'RE ON THE
SHOW.
WHEN WE COME BACK, BREAK OUT
YOUR WEST WING DEPARTURE BINGO
CARDS, BILL SHINE IS OUT AFTER
LESS THAN A REPORT.
NEW REPORTING REVEALS HOW THE
FOX NEWS ALUM MANAGED TO WIND UP
ON TRUMP'S BAD SIDE IN THE BEAT
OF AN EYE.
ALSO A MOLE INSIDE THE WHITE
HOUSE WHO LEAKED THE DIRT ON
JARED AND IVANKA'S SECURITY
CLEARANCE TO INVESTIGATORS IN
CONGRESS, AND HE'S NOT EVEN IN
THE RACE YET BUT THE HITS
AGAINST JOE BIDEN ARE ALREADY
COMING.
I SPOKE TO ONE PROMINENT
DEMOCRAT WHO'S SAYING THANKS BUT
NO THANKS.
WE'LL SEE THAT VIDEO A LITTLE
BIT LATER SO STAY WITH US.
WE'VE GOT A LOT COMING.
STAY WI.
WE'VE GOT A LOT COMING
WE DON'T FOLLOW THE NAYSAYERS.
♪ ♪ ♪
♪♪
♪ Do you
love me? ♪
♪ I can
really move ♪
♪ Do you love me? ♪
♪ I'm in the groove ♪
♪ Now do you love me? ♪
♪ Do you love me
now that I can dance? ♪
Applebee's
3 Course Meal.
Now that's
Eatin' Good
in the Neighborhood.
No more excuses
with Cologuard.
We all make excuses for the
things we don't want to do.
But when it comes to
colon cancer screening...
I'm not doin' that.
I eat plenty of kale.
Ahem, as I was saying...
...with Cologuard,
you don't need an excuse...
All that prep?
No thanks.
That drink tastes horrible!
But...there's no
prep with Cologuard...
I can't take the
time off work.
Who has two days?
And I feel fine -
no symptoms!
Everybody, listen!
All you need is a
trip to the bathroom.
If you're 50 or older
and at average risk,
Cologuard is the
noninvasive option
that finds 92%
of colon cancers.
You just get the
kit in the mail,
go to the bathroom,
collect your sample,
then ship it to the lab!
This is your year!
Own it!
Cologuard is not right
for everyone.
It is not for high
risk individuals,
including those with a
history of colon cancer
or precancer, IBD, certain
hereditary cancer syndromes,
or a family history
of colon cancer.
Ask your doctor if Cologuard
is right for you.
Covered by Medicare and
most major insurers.
Ask your doctor if Cologuard
is right for you.
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM SAYS
YOU CAN'T MAKE A
400 HORSEPOWER SEDAN,
THAT'S ALSO
ENVIRONMENTALLY CONSCIOUS.
WE DON'T FOLLOW
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>> THE REVOLVING DOOR OF WHITE
HOUSE COMMUNICATIONS DIRECTOR
JUST KEEPS ON SPINNING.
TRUMP'S 5th COMMUNICATIONS
DIRECTOR IS OUT.
BILL SHINE, HE'S RESIGNING AFTER
SERVING IN THE POSITION FOR JUST
EIGHT MONTHS, WHICH BY TRUMP'S
STANDARDS IS, APPROXIMATELY 22
SCARAMUCCIS, THE LONGEST ANYONE
HAS HELD THIS POSITION UNDER
TRUMP.
HE SOLIDIFIED THE PRSIDENT'S
TIES.
MR. SHINES PRESENCE IN THE WHITE
HOUSE WAS SEEN AS HOW EMBLEMATIC
TRUMP HAS ALIGNED HIMSELF WITH
FOX, AND EMBRACING LINES OF
ARGUMENT THAT ADVANCED ON BEHALF
OF HIS POLICIES AND PRESIDENCY.
AS "THE WASHINGTON POST"
REPORTS, QUOTE IN RECENT MONTHS,
TRUMP HAS COMPLAINED ABOUT HIS
MEDIA COVERAGE AND BLAMED SHINE
FOR NOT MAKING IF MORE POSITIVE
ACCORDING TO CURRENT AND FORMER
ADMINISTRATION OFFICIALS.
JOINING ME NOW ON THE SET IS
FORMER OBAMA CAMPAIGN MANAGER
AND DEPUTY WHITE HOUSE CHIEF OF
STAFF JIM MESSINA AND JENNIFER
REUBEN, MSNBC CONTRIBUTOR, MATT
MILLER AND PHIL RUCKER ARE STILL
WITH US.
PHIL, I WANT TO START WITH YOU,
I BELIEVE THE LAST THING I READ
IS FROM A PIECE YOU WROTE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> TELL US ABOUT WHY NOW THE
MOMENT ARRIVED FOR BILL SHINE'S
EXIT?
>> YEAH, JOHN, WELL, IT WAS A
PRETTY ABRUPT ANNOUNCEMENT TODAY
BUT NOT ALL TOGETHER SURPRISING.
WE KNOW JUST FROM OUR REPORTING
THE LAST SEVERAL MONTHS THAT
TRUMP AND SHINE HAVE NOT BEEN
SEEING EYE TO EYE ENTIRELY.
IN PART BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT
EXPECTED THAT BY BRINGING IN
BILL SHINE, THE FORMER FOX NEWS
PRESIDENT, HE WAS GOING TO
SOMEHOW IMPROVE HIS MEDIA
COVERAGE THAT THE NEWS NARRATIVE
ABOUT THE TRUMP PRESIDENCY WOULD
SOMEHOW EVOLVE INTO A MUCH
GREATER PLACE FOR TRUMP AND THAT
JUST DIDN'T HAPPEN.
SHINE DOESN'T HAVE A MAGIC WAND.
HE CAME IN TO DO THIS JOB BUT AT
THE END OF THE DAY, THE
PRESIDENT IS THE PRESIDENT, AND
THE NEWS MEDIA LIKE OURSELVES,
WE'RE JUST COVERING WHAT THE
PRESIDENT DOES.
HE GREW FRUSTRATED WITH SHINE.
THEY WERE NOT SORT OF NATURAL,
YOU KNOW, THERE WASN'T A LOT OF
NATURAL CHEMISTRY THERE, AND I
THINK AT THE END OF THE DAY,
THEY DECIDED TO GO SEPARATE WAYS
AND SHINE, IT'S IMPORTANT TO
POINT OUT IS STAYING IN THE
ORBIT.
HE'S GOING TO BE AN ADVISER TO
THE REELECTION CAMPAIGN, OF
COURSE NO LONGER IN THE WHITE
HOUSE.
>> IN ANOTHER WORLD, A NORMAL
WORLD, THE WORLD YOU AND I USED
TO INHABIT, IT WAS NOT AN
UNCONVENTIONAL THING, A COUPLE
OF YEARS INTO AN ADMINISTRATION.
YOU START TO TURN YOUR EYES
TOWARD REELECTION.
THERE WOULD BE SOME PEOPLE WHO
WERE WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS WHO
WOULD LEAVE THE WHITE HOUSE AND
WORK ON THE CAMPAIGN.
I BELIEVE THAT HAPPENED IN YOUR
WHITE HOUSE RIGHT AROUND THIS
TIME.
WHY SHOULD WE NOT THINK THAT
THIS IS JUST, YOU KNOW, GETTING
READY FOR REELECTION AS OPPOSED
TO KIND OF THE WAY IT'S BEING
PORTRAYED IS SHINE GOT FIRED AND
THIS JOB ON THE CAMPAIGN IS A
SPACE SAVING GESTURE.
>> THE CAMPAIGN IS THE PLACE
WHERE THEY GO TO DUMP THE
BODIES.
YOU GET FIRED FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE.
THEY PUT YOU ON THE REELECTION
CAMPAIGN, AND I DON'T BLAME THIS
GUY.
I HAVE NEVER MET BILL SHINE.
THEY'RE LASTING A HUNDRED DAYS
FOR A VERY GOOD REASON, EVERY
MORNING THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES WAKES UP AND BLOWS
UP THEIR COMMUNICATIONS PLAN
WHEN HE GETS ON TWITTER.
THAT JOB IS IMPOSSIBLE.
NO ONE CAN STAY THERE BECAUSE
YOU HAVE AN ERRATIC LEADER AT
THE TOP, AND THEY CAN PUT A NEW
PERSON IN THE JOB, WE'RE ABOUT
TO GET OUR FOURTH CHIEF OF
STAFF, FIVE COMMUNICATIONS
DIRECTORS, MORE LAWYERS THAN YOU
AND I CAN COUNT AND BECAUSE THE
ROT BEGINS AT THE TOP.
>> I ASK YOU JENNIFER, ONE OF
THE THINGS, BUT LET ME READ A
LITTLE BIT FROM THIS PIECE IN
THE NEW YORKER, YOU WERE QUOTED
IN IT, AND THIS PIECE RUNG A LOT
OF BELLS THIS WEEKEND, NOW WITH
SHINE GOING OUT, IT SEEMS
INCREDIBLY WELL TIMED OR ONE OF
THE THINGS THAT PRECIPITATED THE
DEPARTURE.
A SOURCE CLOSE TO TRUMP SAYS
THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN
COMPLAINING THAT SHINE HASN'T
BEEN AGGRESSIVE ENOUGH.
LATE LAST YEAR TRUMP TOLD THE
SOURCE SHINE PROMISED ME PRESS
COVERAGE WOULD GET BETTER BUT
IT'S GOTTEN WORSE.
TRUMP THOUGHT HE WAS GETTING
ROGER AILES BUT INSTEAD HE GOT
ROGER AILES GOPHER.
TALK ABOUT THIS A LITTLE BIT,
AND THE SHINE PERPLEX.
>> YES, WELL, SHINE OF COURSE
WAS THE PERSON WHO WAS THE CLEAN
UP GUY.
HE WENT AROUND AND CLEANED UP
THE MESSES FROM ROGER AILES,
FROM BILL O'REILLY, FROM ALL OF
THEM.
YOU KNOW, HE IS NOT THE GUY WHO
MAKES THE PRETTY PICTURES, HE'S
THE GUY WHO MANAGES THE TALENT
WHO HELPED TRUMP GET ELECTED.
SO PERHAPS TRUMP DIDN'T EXACTLY
GET WHAT HE WANTED BUT AS JIM
SAID NO ONE IS GOING TO GET HIM
WHAT HE WANTS, TRUMP IS TRUMP
AND HE'S GOING TO GO DO HIS OWN
THING.
I THINK IT'S VERY POSSIBLE THAT
THE ARTICLE KIND OF WAS THE
TIPPING POINT FOR TRUMP.
IF THERE'S ONE THING TRUMP HATES
IT'S TO BE PORTRAYED AS
SOMEONE'S PAWN, AND HE HATES
THAT KIND OF STUFF, SO THAT
COULD WELL HAVE BEEN THE FINAL
STRAW.
>> IT STRIKES ME AS SORT OF
SCANDALOUS, I'LL STICK WITH YOU,
ONE OF THE THINGS JANE WROTE
ABOUT IN THIS PIECE, BILL SHINE
WAS MORE PERSONALLY INVOLVED
WITH COVERING UP THE RECORD OF
ROGER AILES WITH RESPECT TO
SEXUAL HARASSMENT IN THE
WORKPLACE THAN ANY OTHER SINGLE
PERSON THAT I KNOW OF, AND IT'S
AMAZING TO ME THAT HE GLIDED
INTO THIS JOB WITH ALMOST NO
COMMENT ABOUT THAT, DID NOT
BECOME A MATTER OF PUBLIC
CONTROVERSY THAT BILL SHINE WAS
GOING TO THE WHITE HOUSE GIVEN
SOME OF THE DARK PARTS HE HAD
DONE AT FOX NEWS.
HE WAS INVOLVED IN SOME OF THE
DIRTIEST STUFF.
>> HE WENT TO WORK FOR A GUY WHO
PAID OFF TWO WOMEN WITH SLUSH
MONEY, A LINEUP OF 19 WOMEN
DURING THE CAMPAIGN WHO MADE
ALLEGATIONS OF HARASSMENT.
THIS IS A GUY WHO STUCK BY ROB
PORTER, THE WHITE HOUSE STAFF
SECRETARY AFTER IT HAD BEEN
REVEALED, REALLY HORRIBLE
PICTURES OF BATTERY ON HIS WIFE.
AND HE WAS THE GUY OF COURSE WHO
WENT OUT AND ENDORSED ROI MOORE.
THE PRESIDENT IS A WALKING
DISASTER IN THIS AREA, AND SO
EVERYONE SORT OF LIKE PALES BY
COMPARISON.
THIS IS PART OF THE TRUMP
PHENOMENON.
HE HAS BROUGHT US ALL DOWN TO
THIS BASE LEVEL SO THIS NO
LONGER RINGS ALARM BELLS AND
PRACTICALLY ANYONE CAN WALK IN
THE DOOR.
TRUMP WALKED IN THE DOOR, WHY
NOT HIM.
>> TRUMP DOESN'T LIKE TO BE SEEN
AS A STOOJ OR PUPPET, AND THE
NOTION HE'S BEING PUSHED AROUND
OR CONTROLLED BY OUTSIDE FORCES
ANNOYS HIM.
THIS STORY POINTED OUT THE
EXTENT TO WHICH TRUMP IS IN
CONSTANT COMMUNICATION WITH SEAN
HANNITY, THERE'S THE BILL SHINE
ELEMENT TO THE STORY, AND YET
TODAY WE HAVE TRUMP ON TWITTER
TWEETING THANK YOU AT FOX AND
FRIENDS, GREAT SHOW.
SO IT DOESN'T SEEM AS THOUGH,
TRUMP MAY HAVE GOTTEN SICK OF
BILL SHINE BUT THAT STORY AND
THE CONTROVERSY AROUND IT DOES
NOT SEEM TO HAVE TURNED DONALD
TRUMP AGAINST FOX NEWS.
>> I DON'T KNOW THAT WE'RE EVER
GOING TO SEE TRUMP TURN AGAINST
FOX NEWS AS LONG AS, YOU KNOW,
THE TALENT ON FOX CONTINUES TO
PRAISE HIS PRESIDENCY, AND HIS
AGENDA.
IN MANY WAYS, SHINE WAS THE
NEXUS, HE WAS THE GLUE THAT
BROUGHT THE WHITE HOUSE AND FOX
TOGETHER.
IT WAS SHINE WHO HELPED ARRANGE
FOR SEAN HANNITY TO DO THESE
INTERVIEWS IS AT ALL OF THE BIG
INTERNATIONAL SUMMITS AND TO BE
ALONGSIDE THE PRESIDENT AS HE
TOURED THE BORDER DOWN IN TEXAS
A WEEK OR TWO AGO, A MONTH OR
TWO AGO, RATHER, SO SHINE PLAYED
THAT ROLE, BUT SOMEBODY ELSE IS
GOING TO STEP IN AND PLAY THAT
ROLE GOING FORWARD.
IT'S NOT LIKE THERE'S GOING TO
BE A BREACH BETWEEN TRUMP AND
HIS FAVORITE NETWORK.
>> WE ALL KNOW THAT TRUMP REALLY
OWN TALKS FOX NEWS BUT IT'S
STRIKING TO SEE THE GRAPHIC.
LET'S PUT THIS UP, THE NUMBERS
ON THE INTERVIEWS, NETWORK
INTERVIEWS WITH DONALD TRUMP,
FOX NEWS, 44.
ABC NEWS, CBS NEWS, 10.
>> THE PRESIDENT HAD CERTAIN NET
WORKS HE LIKED BETTER THAN
OTHERS BUT THOSE NUMBERS ARE
STUNNING.
>> IT IS UNBELIEVABLE AND WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN EVENTUALLY IS
WE'RE GOING TO GET INTO A
REELECTION CAMPAIGN.
IF YOU ADD UP THE VIEWERSHIP,
HE'S NOW NOT COMMUNICATING TO A
WHOLE BUNCH OF VOTERS WHO ARE
SITTING THERE TRYING TO MAKE UP
THEIR MIND.
IT'S NOT LIKE THEY'RE GOING TO
FORGET IT.
GREAT, NOW WE WANT TO BE YOUR
SPOKESPERSON.
THERE'S ONE OTHER POINT.
THE WHITE HOUSE HAS HAD ONE
PRESS CONFERENCE IN 2019, AND SO
THEIR PRESS OPERATION IS FOX
NEWS, THE WAY THEY COMMUNICATE
IS THROUGH FOX NEWS AND IT'S NOW
AN EXTENSION OF THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> AND DONALD TRUMP HAS 38% IR
REDUCIBLE CORE, INCREDIBLY HIGH
FLOOR, AND INCREDIBLY LOW
CEILING.
>> HE'S ONLY TALKING TO HIS
BASE.
>> THAT IS AN INCREDIBLY
INTERESTING CONVERSATION.
AFTER THIS BREAK, WE HAVE TO DO
A COMMERCIAL HERE.
THE LEAKS ARE COMING FROM INSIDE
THE WHITE HOUSE.
NOT JUST INSIDE THE HOUSE,
INSIDE THE WHITE HOUSE.
THE OBJECTION THE CONGRESSIONAL
SCRUTINY MAY HAVE BEEN IN VAIN.
THAT'S COMING UP NEXT.
N VAIN
-Oh, n-no.
-Look, [Sighs] I get it.
Some new guy comes in
helping your mom bundle and save
with Progressive,
but hey,
we're all in this together.
Right, champ?
-I'm getting more nuggets.
-How about some carrots?
You don't want
to ruin your dinner.
-You're not my dad!
-That's fair.
Overstepped.
>>> WE HAD A LITTLE BIT OF A GUT
PUNCH FOR THE WHITE HOUSE.
THE ADMINISTRATION DREW A LINE
IN THE SAND REFUSING THE REQUEST
FOR DOCUMENTS RELATED TO THE
SAGA OF JARED KUSHNER'S SECURITY
CLEARANCE.
AS IT TURNS OUT THE COMMITTEE
MAY HAVE HAD THOSE DOCUMENTS ALL
ALONG.
AXIOS IS REPORTING THAT SOMEONE
INSIDE THE WHITE HOUSE HAD
ALREADY LEAKED THEM TO CONGRESS.
NOT ONLY IS THE LEAK GOING TO BE
PROBLEMATIC FOR TEAM TRUMP.
THEY'RE EVIDENTLY RECKONING WITH
THE LEAKER AS WELL, ONE WHO HAS
MOVED BY SCOOPS TO JOURNALISTS
AND HANDING SCOOPS TO CONGRESS.
WHY IT MATTERS, QUOTE, THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S PROBLEMS WITH
LEAKS WILL NOW BENEFIT CONGRESS
MAKING IT HARDER FOR THE WHITE
HOUSE TO WITHHOLD INFORMATION
FROM DEMOCRATIC INVESTIGATORS.
JOINING US NOW AT THE TABLE WITH
MY OTHER TWO FRIENDS, REVEREND
AL SHARPTON, THE HOST OF
POLITICS NATION HERE ON MSNBC.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> PHIL, I WANT TO START BY
ASKING YOU THIS QUESTION, IF THE
HOUSE COMMITTEE ALREADY HAD
THESE DOCUMENTS, WHY ARE THEY
ASKING FOR THEM?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW.
IT MIGHT BE THAT THEY'RE TRYING
TO GET MORE DOCUMENTS,
ADDITIONAL DOCUMENTATION ON THE
SAME TOPIC.
IT MIGHT BE THAT THEY'RE TRYING
TO FORMALIZE THEIR REQUEST
BECAUSE THEY OBTAINED THE
DOCUMENTS NOT THROUGH SORT OF
THE FRONT DOOR OF THE WHITE
HOUSE.
>> RIGHT.
>> I'M NOT SURE.
ONE THING WE SHOULD KEEP IN MIND
IS THIS SEEMS TO BE ONLY THE
BEGINNING OF THE HOUSE DEMOCRATS
INVESTIGATIONS INTO IVANKA TRUMP
AND JARED KUSHNER, THERE ARE
DISCUSSIONS UNDERWAY ABOUT
LAUNCHING PROBES INTO A NUMBER
OF OTHER WAYS, INCLUDING IF
IVANKA TRUMP ENRICHED HERSELF
AND HER COMPANY USING HER
POSITION AS A GOVERNMENT
EMPLOYEE.
>> WHAT'S MORE PROBLEMATIC, THE
FACT THAT THE DOCUMENTS WERE
LEAKED AND WHAT'S IN THEM OR THE
FACT THAT THE WHITE HOUSE HAS A
MOLE WILLING TO COUGH UP THE
DOCUMENTS TO DEMOCRATIC
INVESTIGATORS.
>> THE THING THAT ALWAYS
SEPARATES AN INVESTIGATION THAT
PRODUCES DAMAGING REVELATIONS,
MAYBE E-MAILS THAT SHOW
MISCONDUCT OR INAPPROPRIATE
LANGUAGE, AND THE ONES THAT ARE
TRULY EXPLOSIVE, THE ONES THAT
BECOME FRONT PAGE NEWS AND LEAD
TO RESIGNATIONS AND DEPARTURES,
THE DIFFERENCE IS WHISTLE
BLOWERS, IT'S WHEN YOU HAVE A
WHISTLE BLOWER THAT CAN COME
FORWARD AND TELL CONGRESSIONAL
INVESTIGATORS WHERE TO LOOK,
WHAT QUESTIONS THEY OUGHT TO BE
ASKING AND SECOND OF ALL, TO
TAKE AWAY ONE OF THE WHITE
HOUSES MOST POWERFUL WEAPONS,
WHICH IS THE ABILITY TO DELAY
TURNING OVER DOCUMENTS AND TO
FIGHT IT IN COURT.
IF THEY CAN GET THE DOCUMENTS
FROM A WHISTLE BLOWER, IT TAKES
AWAY THE ABOUT TO DRAG OUT FOR
MONTHS AND YEARS, AND GETS RIGHT
TO THE HEART OF THE MANNER, AND
THE FINAL THING IT GIVES YOU IS
SOMETIMES A FACE TO PUT IN A
CONGRESSIONAL HEARING, AND IT'S
EXTREMELY DAMAGING FOR AN
ADMINISTRATION.
>> A LOT OF NODDING HEADS,
EVERYONE IS ABOUT TO JUMP OUT OF
THEIR SKINS.
JENNIFER GO.
>> EVERYTHING HE SAID, YES, I
WOULD ALSO SAY THIS, THERE ARE A
LOT OF PEOPLE WHO HAVE HAD A
PENT UP DESIRE TO TELL WHAT THEY
HAVE TO SAY.
THEY HAVE NOT HAD A DEMOCRATIC
CONGRESS, AND NOW THEY HAVE ONE.
THEY HAVE SOMEONE TO GIVE THE
INFORMATION TO.
SO AGAIN, THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING THAT HAS HAPPENED IN THIS
ADMINISTRATION WAS THE CHANGE IN
CONGRESS.
I THINK ONE OF THE OTHER ISSUES
THAT WE'RE GOING TO SEE HERE IS,
YOU KNOW, THESE TWO WERE NOT
SUCH POPULAR CHILDREN IN THE
WHITE HOUSE.
THEY WERE GIVEN HUGE, VAST, YOU
KNOW, AREAS OF EXPERTISE FOR
WHICH THEY HAD NO EXPERIENCE.
THEY ABSOLUTELY, FROM WHAT WE
HAVE SEEN, USED THESE
OPPORTUNITIES TO FURTHER
THEMSELVES.
THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE WHO I
AM SURE RESENT THIS, AND THEY
ARE MORE THAN HAPPY TO CHITCHAT,
AND THE NOTION THAT THE
DEMOCRATS SHOULD BE AFRAID OF
GOING AFTER THE CHILDREN, THE
CHILDREN ARE THERE BECAUSE OF
NEPOTISM, BECAUSE OF CONFLICTS
OF INTEREST, OF COURSE YOU HAVE
TO GO AFTER THEM.
GUYS, COME ON, GROW A SPINE.
>> YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO SAY.
>> PHIL GAVE YOU TWO GOOD
REASONS, LET ME GIVE YOU THE
THIRD, THE FORMER GUY WHO TRIED
TO PLUG THE LEAKS IN THE WHITE
HOUSE.
>> I REMEMBER THAT.
>> YOU USED TO DO THAT
OCCASIONALLY.
>> WE'LL HAVE A WHOLE SHOW ABOUT
THAT.
THEY DON'T WANT TO SAY WHO GAVE
IT TO THEM, RIGHT, ESPECIALLY
THIS DOCUMENT, TO MATT'S POINT,
THIS DOCUMENT ONLY FIVE OR SIX
PEOPLE WOULD HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
SEE.
THIS IS A REALLY EXCLUSIVE
DOCUMENT AND IT'S GOING TO BE
PRETTY OBVIOUS WHO GAVE IT TO
CONGRESS.
I'M SURE CONGRESS IS LIKE LET'S
GO GET IT THE OFFICIAL CHANNEL
SO IT'S NOT OBVIOUS JOE GAVE US
THIS THING.
WHEN THESE THINGS ARE LEAKING,
HOUSTON, YOU HAVE A PROBLEM.
>> I WANT TO COME BACK TO THE
POINT, JENNIFER GOES TO THE
QUESTION OF CAN YOU GO TOO FAR,
AND THE QUESTION OF THE KIDS.
I WANT TO READ FROM THIS
"WASHINGTON POST" PIECE OF WHICH
RUCKER IS ONE OF THE COAUTHORS.
HOUSE DEMOCRATS ARE TORN, AN
AREA OF INQUIRY THAT WOULD
INFLAME TENSIONS WITH TRUMP.
HIGHLIGHT THE CONCERN AMONG SOME
DEMOCRATS ABOUT THE POLITICAL
OPTICS OF QUESTIONING TRUMP'S
ADULT CHILDREN, EVEN AS THEY B
CYST THE PRESIDENT -- INSIST THE
PRESIDENT'S FAMILY MEMBERS
ESPECIALLY THOSE SERVING IN
GOVERNMENT SHOULD NOT BE IMMUNE
FROM ACCOUNTABILITY.
JENNIFER SAID NO ONE SHOULD HAVE
HESITANCY ABOUT THIS, YOUR SENSE
IS IN FACT AMONG DEMOCRATS THERE
IS SOME DEGREE OF DIVISION AND
DISSENSION OVER EXACTLY HOW FAR
TO PUSH.
TALK ABOUT THAT.
>> I THINK IT'S LESS OVER A
DIVIDE ABOUT WHETHER TO
INVESTIGATE OR IT'S HOW HARD AND
HOW TO DO IT, WHAT'S THAT TIME
LINE LIKE.
DO YOU SUBPOENA THEM, DO YOU
CALL THEM FORWARD TO TESTIFY.
DO YOU START SLOWLY.
THEY'RE JUST AWARE OF THE
OPTICS.
THESE ARE NOT CHILDREN.
THEY'RE NOT TEENAGERS.
THEY'RE NOT NAIVE AND INVOLVED
IN POLITICS.
THEY ARE WORKING IN GOVERNMENT
AT THE HIGHEST LEVELS AND
OVERSEEING IN THE CASE OF JARED
KUSHNER, OUR COUNTRY'S NATIONAL
SECURITY, AND FOREIGN AFFAIRS,
AND SO THEY'RE VERY MUCH, YOU
KNOW, SUBJECT TO CONGRESSIONAL
OVERSIGHT.
>> REVEREND AL, I WANT TO ASK
YOU THIS QUESTION, AND READ A
QUOTE FROM NANCY PELOSI THAT
AGREES PRETTY MUCH JENNIFER
REUBEN, NANCY PELOSI AGREE,
SOMETHING MUST BE RIGHT.
WHOMEVER FALLS INTO THAT NET
FALLS INTO THAT NET.
THEY ARE ADVISERS TO THE
PRESIDENT.
THEY HAVE SECURITY CLEARANCES,
THIS IS NOT THEIR CHILDREN AT
HOME.
>> AND I THINK THAT WAS CRITICAL
HERE.
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT PEOPLE THAT
WERE GIVING A SECURITY
CLEARANCE.
YOU CAN'T HAVE IT BOTH WAYS.
YOU CAN'T PLAY THAT I'M DADDY'S
LITTLE DAUGHTER AND MY HUSBAND,
BUT I'VE GOT ALL OF THIS KIND OF
SECURITY CLEARANCE, ALL THIS
KIND OF OF INFLUENCE.
YOU'RE EITHER ONE OR THE OTHER.
BUT I THINK THAT WHAT CAUSED A
LOT OF NERVOUSNESS AROUND THE
WHITE HOUSE, WHEN YOU HEAR ABOUT
SOMEBODY LEAKING IS THEY DON'T
KNOW WHAT ELSE THEY LEAKED AND
WHAT MAY BE THE QUESTIONING IF
THEY'RE CALLED BEFORE CONGRESS,
AND IF YOU HAVE PEOPLE AT THE
HIGHEST LEVEL AS WAS SAID ONLY
FOUR OR FIVE WOULD KNOW IT.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE THEY
HAVE, AND YOU KNOW WHAT KIND OF
DEALS THAT THESE PEOPLE HAVE THE
CAPACITY TO CUT.
SO I WOULD BE VERY CONCERNED IF
I WAS THEM TO KNOW PEOPLE AT A
HIGHER LEVEL ARE GETTING THEM
THINGS.
WE KNOW WHAT WE THINK THEY MAY
HAVE ON SECURITY STUFF.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE HAS
BEEN LEAKED ABOUT JARED KUSHNER
AND IVANKA'S POSSIBLE DEALINGS.
>> I WILL SAY THE DEMOCRATS,
THIS IS GOING TO BE A RECURRING
THEME GOING FORWARD, THAT
DEMOCRATS ARE ARGUING AND
WORRIED ABOUT EVERY QUESTION IF
THEY'RE GOING TO OVERREACH ON
SPECIFIC THINGS.
THERE IS ONE AREA I DON'T THINK
THEY SHOULD WORRY ABOUT.
PHIL RUCKER, THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR BEING ON THE SHOW AS ALWAYS.
YOU ARE AWESOME.
AFTER THE BREAK WE'LL HAVE A
DISCUSSION OF WAITING FOR JOE
BIDEN TO CHALLENGE DONALD TRUMP,
IS OUT THE DOOR AND AROUND THE
CORNER, THE FORMER VICE
PRESIDENT COULD CHANGE
EVERYTHING WITH A SNAP OF HIS
FINGERS.
HOW LIKELY IS THAT MAN TO RUN
ACCORDING TO HIM, NEXT.
TO RUN
ACCORDING TO HIM, NEXT
My name is Austin,
I am a two-time
brain cancer conqueror.
There are some days
when I have my, my downs
and then I have to rely on
my mom to come
pick me up from work.
We need to be connected
on a regular basis.
Sometimes I get
hundreds of texts from her
and I'm like stop.
I owe everything to her,
she's my world.
I love you mom.
I love you too.
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now comes with
Apple Music on us.
Get a free Galaxy S10e
when you buy the new Galaxy S10.
Only on Verizon.
You might take something
for your heart...
or joints.
But do you take something
for your brain.
With an ingredient originally
discovered in jellyfish,
Prevagen has been shown
in clinical trials
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
♪♪
A wealth of information.
A wealth of perspective.
♪♪
A wealth of opportunities.
That's the clarity you get from
Fidelity Wealth Management.
Straightforward advice,
tailored recommendations,
tax-efficient
investing strategies,
and a dedicated advisor
to help you grow
and protect your wealth.
Fidelity Wealth Management.
to help you grow
and protect your wealth.
IF YOU HAVE A GARDEN YOU KNOW,
WEEDS ARE LOWDOWN
LITTLE SCOUNDRELS.
DON'T STOOP TO THEIR LEVEL.
DRAW THE LINE WITH THE
ROUNDUP SURE SHOT WAND.
IT EXTENDS WITH A
PROTECTIVE SHIELD
AND TARGETS WEEDS
MORE PRECISELY.
IT LETS YOU KILL WHAT'S BAD
RIGHT DOWN TO THE ROOT
WHILE GUARDING THE GOOD.
ROUNDUP SURE SHOT WAND.
GOT WEEDS IN YOUR GRASS TOO?
TRY ROUNDUP FOR LAWNS.
KILLS WEEDS, NOT THE LAWN.
ROUNDUP BRAND.
TRUSTED FOR OVER 40 YEARS.
>>> THE FIELD OF DEMOCRATIC
CONTENDERS FOR 2020 IS AMONG THE
LARGEST AND MOST DIVERSE THAT WE
HAVE EVER SEEN.
THIS WEEK WE SAW MORE PEOPLE
COME OUT AND SAY THEY WON'T RUN
THAN THOSE WHO SAY THEY WILL.
ONE PROMINENT DEMOCRAT WHO
WEIGHED IN ON THE CROWDED FIELD
IS NEW YORK CITY MAYOR BILL DE
BLASIO.
HE WEIGHED IN WITH ME WHEN I SAT
DOWN WITH HIM THIS WEEK.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
>> THIS WEEK, YOUR PREDECESSOR
MICHAEL BLOOMBERG DECIDES NOT TO
RUN.
YOU COULD ARGUE THERE'S NOT A
SINGLE HUMAN BEING IN THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY WHO HAS DONE
MORE ON CLIMATE AND GUNS THAN
MIKE.
.
AND YET DESPITE ALL OF THAT, HE
WITH HIS MONEY AND POLITICAL
BRAINS AROUND HIM, ALL THOSE
PEOPLE, THEY ALL LOOK TO THE
STATE OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
RIGHT NOW AND SAID, HE HAS NO
CHANCE TO BE THE NOMINEE.
SO FIRST OF ALL, DO YOU THINK
THAT'S RIGHT?
>> 110%.
>> HE HAD NO CHANCE?
>> NO CHANCE.
>> BECAUSE WE'RE A PROGRESSIVE
PARTY MORE AND MORE THAT IS
DESPERATELY TROUBLED BY THE
WEALTH AND POWER CONCENTRATED IN
THE HANDS OF 1%.
AND WE KNOW THAT HAS TO CHANGE
AND IT HAS TO CHANGE QUICKLY, SO
HOW ON EARTH ARE YOU GOING TO
NOMINATE ONE OF THE EIGHT
RICHEST MEN IN THE WORLD.
THAT IS NOT SOMEONE WHO'S GOING
TO CHANGE THAT REALITY.
>> A PLUTOCRAT IS NOT GOING TO
WIN.
.
SO HE MADE THE RIGHT DECISION.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> IS JOE BIDEN A PROGRESSIVE OR
A MODERATE?
>> JOE BIDEN, FIRST OF ALL, A
VERY IMPRESSIVE PUBLIC SERVANT,
BUT, I CERTAINLY CONSIDER HIM A
MODERATE.
>> SO CAN'T BE THE NOMINEE?
>> I DON'T THINK THIS PARTY IS
GOING TO CHOOSE A MODERATE.
I DON'T THINK THIS PARTY SHOULD
CHOOSE A MODERATE.
IF A MODERATE RUNS AND WINS,
THIS VERY DANGEROUS STATUS QUO
WILL CONTINUE.
WE HAVE AN INCOME AND EQUALITY
CRISIS THAT IS DANGEROUS AND
DESTABLING.
>> BUT YOU HAVE A LOT OF RESPECT
FOR JOE BIDEN AS A PUBLIC
SERVANT.
>> 100%.
>> WE COULD SAY HE WOULD NOT WIN
THE DE BLASIO ENFORCEMENT.
HE'S A MODERATE.
>> LOOK, I HAVE A LOT OF RESPECT
TO HIM, BUT IF YOU SAY WHAT DOES
THIS PARTY NEED RIGHT NOW, IT
DOESN'T NEED A MODERATE.
WHAT DOES THIS COUNTRY NEED, IT
AND HE'S A MODERATE.
>> SO BILL DE BLASIO WHO HIMSELF
IS THINKING ABOUT RUNNING FOR
PRESIDENT, HEADING TO SOUTH
CAROLINA THIS WEEKEND, HE'S BEEN
IN IOWA.
WHO KNOWS HOW REAL THAT IS, BUT
HE'S THE VERY LIBERAL MAYOR OF
THE BIGGEST CITY IN AMERICA, AND
HAS HAD A SUCCESSFUL RUN HERE.
HE'S GOING TO HAVE A ROLE.
HIS ENDORSEMENT IS GOING TO
MATTER.
HE SAID JOE BIDEN SHOULD NEVER
GET NOMINATED.
HE SAYS JOE BIDEN PROBABLY
SHOULDN'T RUN EITHER BECAUSE
THIS PARTY IS SO FAR TO THE LEFT
NOW THAT THERE'S NO WAY THAT JOE
BIDEN COULD GET NOMINATED IS
THAT RIGHT?
>> NO, I UNDERSTAND THE ARGUMENT
BUT IT'S NOT TRUE.
60% OF THE DEMOCRATS SAY THE
MOST IMPORTANT ISSUE IS WHO CAN
BEAT DONALD TRUMP.
DONALD TRUMP IS A UNIFYING
FACTOR.
YOU REMEMBER IN 2004, WE DANCED
WITH HOWARD DEAN, AND JOHN
EDWARDS AND KERRY CAN BEAT BUSH
AND WE'RE GOING TO KERRY.
THE SECOND THING IS THERE'S NO
MAJOR FRONT RUNNER IN THIS RACE
BIDEN INCLUDED BUT THE THOUGHT
THAT WE'RE GOING TO GO TO THE
MOST PROGRESSIVE CANDIDATE IS
PROBABLY NOT TRUE.
THE OTHER THING IS AS YOU HAVE
COVERED, SEVEN STATES HAVE GONE
FROM CAUCUSES TO OPEN PRIMARIES
IN THE 2020 ELECTION, WHICH IS
GOING TO OPEN IT UP TO A MUCH
BIGGER GROUP OF PEOPLE INCLUDING
INDEPENDENTS AND REPUBLICANS IN
A DEMOCRATIC PRIMARY AND LIKELY
GO TO ELECTING OR NOMINATING A
MORE ELECTABLE CANDIDATE IN THE
GENERAL ELECTION.
>> YOU RAN IN 2004.
YOU WERE PRETTY PROGRESSIVE
CANDIDATE IF I REMEMBER
CORRECTLY, MORE IN LINE WITH THE
MAINSTREAM WHERE THE PARTY IS
NOW THAN IT WAS IN 2004, DO YOU
THINK THAT A JOE BIDEN RUNNING
PRIMARILY IN THE WAY THAT JIM
SUGGESTS WHICH NOT GOING TO BE
ON THE FAR LEFT OF THE PARTY,
HE'S NOT GOING TO BE THE
PROGRESSIVE MAINSTREAM BUT HE'S
GOING TO RUN LARGELY ON I'M
GOING TO TAKE OUT DONALD TRUMP.
IS HE GOING TO MAKE A BIG
DIFFERENCE?
>> I THINK I AGREE THAT THE
PARTY HAS MOVED TOWARD THE LEFT,
BUT I THINK THE OVERWHELMING
MAJORITY OF PEOPLE THAT ARE
GOING TO VOTE IN THESE PRIMARIES
ARE GOING TO WANT SOMEONE THAT
CAN BEAT DONALD TRUMP, AND I
THINK THAT, YOU KNOW, I TALKED
TO A LOT OF MY PROGRESSIVE
FRIENDS AND I'M CONSIDERED
PROGRESSIVE, THAT YOU CAN
ELIMINATE A LOT OF PEOPLE IN
THIS.
MANY OF THE PROGRESSIVE
CANDIDATES DO NOT ENERGIZE BLACK
VOTERS AND DO NOT ENERGIZE BROWN
VOTERS.
IF YOU LOOK AT SOME OF THE
RESULTS, THEY LOSE THE BLACK
VOTE.
ACCORDING TO THE MAP AND THE
CALENDAR, YOU GO FROM IOWA TO
NEW HAMPSHIRE TO SOUTH CAROLINA,
SOUTH CAROLINA IS NOT A STATE
THAT'S GOING TO BE LOOKING FOR
THE MOST PROGRESSIVE.
IT'S A STATE WITH A LOT OF BLACK
VOTERS AND YOUR SUPER LEFT GUY
CAN DIE THERE IF THEY DON'T KNOW
HOW TO DEAL WITH ISSUES LIKE
THAT THAT JOE BIDEN DOES KNOW
HOW TO DEAL THAT.
I'M NOT SAYING HE WINS SOUTH
CAROLINA, BUT I'M SAYING THAT
YOU BETTER LOOK AT MAP IF YOU'RE
ON YOUR WAY TO WINNING THE
NOMINATION.
>> THIS MORNING, ON THIS AIR, ON
MORNING JOE, YOU HAD JOHN
HICKENLOOPER, A SELF-E VOWED
MODERATE, MULTIMILLIONAIRE,
ENTREPRENEURIAL SUCCESS STORY,
TAKING OUT THE TURF WHICH IS NOT
THE PROGRESSIVE LANE BUT ASKED
ON THE AIR THIS MORNING WHETHER
HE WAS A CAPITALIST COULD NOT
COME OUT AND SAY I'M A
CAPITALIST.
AGAIN, APPARENTLY AFRAID THAT
SAYING YOU'RE A CAPITALIST IN
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY IS THE KISS
OF DEATH.
WHAT DOES THAT SAY ABOUT WHERE
THINGS ARE?
>> IT SAYS HE'S A BAD CANDIDATE.
THERE ARE GOOD MODERATE
CANDIDATES, BAD MODERATE
CANDIDATES, GOOD PROGRESSIVE,
BAD PROGRESSIVE.
ELIZABETH WARREN HAS SAID I'M A
CAPITALIST, AND THIS IS WHAT WE
HAVE TO DO FOR CAPITALISM TO
HAVE A DECENT HUMANE SOCIETY.
I DON'T THINK
I DON'T THINK HICKEN HOOPER IS
THE GUY TO CARRY THE MESSAGE IF
YOU CAN'T GET THROUGH AN
INTERVIEW ON HIS SECOND DAY OUT
OF THE BOX.
I WOULD ECHO SOMETHING THAT THE
REVEREND SAID.
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY, ALTHOUGH
WE HEAR ABOUT THE MOVE TO THE
LEFT AND THE PROGRESSIVES, WHEN
YOU LOOK AT THE CLEAR DATA,
ALMOST HALF OF THEM CONSIDER
THEMSELVES TO BE CONSERVATIVES
OR MODERATES, IT'S NOT LIKE THE
ENTIRE PARTY HAS BECOME BERNIE
SANDERS OVERNIGHT.
AS THE REVEREND SAID,
YOU ALSO HAVE TO INCLUDE THE
PEOPLE THAT DESPERATELY WANT TO
WIN AND ARE TELLING PEOPLE I
DON'T HAVE TO HAVE MY TOP
FAVORITE, EXCEPT SOMEONE THAT IS
GOOD ENOUGH TO WIN.
I WOULD ALSO ADD THIS.
SAY THAT JOE BIDEN IS A
MODERATE, IT REALLY STRIKES ME
AS PECULIAR.
THEY ACT LIKE THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION WAS SOME
MODERATE OR
REPUBLICAN LIGHT OPERATION.
>> I'LL TELL YOU THAT BILL
DEBLASIO AND MORE SAY THAT THE
OBAMA ADMINISTRATION WAS NOT
PROGRESSIVE ENOUGH AND BILL
CLINTON'S CONSERVATIVE.
WE'LL COME BACK AFTER THIS QUICK
BREAK.
IS QUICK
If you see traces of blood
when you brush or floss,
you don't have to choose
between healthy gums
and strong teeth.
Complete Protection
from parodontax
has 8 designed benefits for
healthy gums and strong teeth.
Complete Protection
from parodontax.
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
Hmm. Exactly.
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay for
what you need.
Nice. But, uh...
what's up with
your... partner?
Oh. Well, we just spend
all day telling everyone
how we customize
car insurance,
because no two people
are alike, so...
LiMu gets a
little confused
when he sees
another bird
that looks
exactly like him.
[ loud crash ]
Yeah.
He'll figure it out.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
♪♪
When cravings hit, hit back.
Choose Glucerna, with
slow release carbs
to help manage blood sugar, and
start making everyday progress.
Glucerna.
All money managers might
seem the same,
but some give their clients
cookie cutter portfolios.
Fisher Investments tailors
portfolios
to your goals and needs.
Some only call when they have
something to sell.
Fisher calls regularly so
you stay informed.
And while some advisors are
happy to earn commissions
whether you do well or not.
Fisher Investments fees
are structured so we do better
when you do better.
Maybe that's why most
of our clients
come from other money managers.
Fisher Investments. Clearly
better money management.
>>> IT IS INTERNATIONAL WOMEN'S
DAY, SO I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT
WE TALK ABOUT ANOTHER ELEMENT OF
THE RACE, BUT IS IDENTITY.
WE HAVE A LOT OF STRONG WOMEN
WHO ARE RUNNING.
ELIZABETH WARREN IS HERE TALKING
ABOUT MANY TECH GIANTS, HOW MUCH
DO YOU THINK BEING A WOMAN IN
DEMOCRATIC RACE IN 2020 IS
ITSELF A HUGE ADVANTAGE?
>> IT IS A HUGE DEAL, RIGHT?
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY WOULD LIKE
TO NOMINATE A WOMAN.
58% OF DEMOCRATIC PRIMARY VOTERS
ARE WOMEN IN THESE BATTLEGROUND
STATES, SO IT'S A BIG ADVANTAGE.
>> I AGREE.
I THINK THAT YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
HAVE A WOMAN ON THE TICKET, IF
NOT THE NOMINEE.
I THINK WE HAVE COME TO THE TIME
IN HISTORY WHERE PEOPLE
SERIOUSLY WANT TO SEE A WOMAN AT
THAT LEVEL OF PRESIDENT, AT
LEAST VICE PRESIDENT.
>> ONE POSITIVE, ONE NEGATIVE,
THE NEGATIVE IS THERE IS A LOT
OF DEMOCRATS TOTALLY SPOOKED BY
THE HILLARY LOSS AND WE HAVE TO
GET A WHITE MAN.
THAT WAS THE FRENZY OVER SHARED
BROWN.
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
ON THE POSITIVE SIDE, WOMEN BY
THE GENERAL PUBLIC ARE LOOKED
UPON AS SAFER BETS.
THEY DON'T DO SOME OF THE STUFF
THAT THESE GUYS HAVE BEEN CAUGHT
DOING.
THEY BEHAVE THEMSELVES IN PUBLIC
AND IN PRIVATE, AND IN SOME
SENSE, IT GIVES A LITTLE BIT
MORE GRAVITAS, AT LEAST I DON'T
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT THAT AT IT
TAKE WARRIOR.
-- TAKEAWAY.
>> MATT MILLER, ONE OF THE
PIECES OF NEWS THIS WEEK WE
HEARD IS THAT YOUR OLD BOSS,
ERIC HOLDER, DECIDED NOT TO RUN.
ARE YOU DISAPPOINTED HE'S NOT
RUNNING?
>> I THINK HE WOULD HAVE BEEN A
GREAT PRESIDENT, BUT THERE IS A
A LOT GOOD CANDIDATES.
HE DECIDED IT'S A BIG HILL TO
CLIMB AND A BIG BURDEN TO ASK OF
YOUR FAMILY.
AND ULTIMATELY DECIDED IT WASN'T
THE RIGHT TIME FOR HIM TO DO IT,
BUT I THINK HE'S GOING TO BE
STAY PRETTY ACTIVE IN POLITICS.
I THINK HE IS RUNNING THIS
REDISTRICTING COALITION AND I
THINK WE WILL SEE HIM POP UP AT
SOME POINT.
>> REAL QUICK, A LITTLE BIRD
TOLD ME THAT BETO O'ROURKE WILL
ANNOUNCE NEXT WEEK.
BETO O'ROURKE GOING TO BE A
SIGNIFICANT PLAYER, YES OR NO?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> I THINK HE IS, BUT HE HAS TO
BROADEN HIS BASE.
HE CANNOT STAY WHERE HE IS.
>> BETO O'ROURKE?
>> YES, HE WILL BE, BUT HE NEEDS
SUBSTANCE AND GRAVITAS.
>> YOU GUYS ARE FANTASTIC.
WHEN YOU SAY SPEED ROUND AT THIS
TABLE, PEOPLE KNOW WHAT IT
MEANS.
WE HAVE ONE MORE BREAK, WE'LL
TAKE THAT BREAK RIGHT NOW AND BE
BACK AFTER THAT.
In a study with Ozempic®,
a majority of adults
lowered their blood sugar
and reached an A1C
of less than seven
and maintained it.
Oh!
Under seven?
And you may lose weight.
In the same
one-year study,
adults lost on average
up to 12 pounds.
Oh!
Up to 12 pounds?
A two-year study showed
that Ozempic® does not
increase the risk
of major cardiovascular events
like heart attack,
stroke, or death.
Oh!
No increased risk?
♪ Oh, oh, oh, Ozempic®! ♪
Ozempic® should not be the first
medicine for treating diabetes,
or for people with
type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not share needles or pens.
Don't reuse needles.
Do not take Ozempic® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine Neoplasia
Syndrome type 2,
or if you are
allergic to Ozempic®.
Stop taking Ozempic®
and get medical help right away
if you get a lump or swelling
in your neck,
severe stomach pain, itching,
rash, or trouble breathing.
Serious side effects
may happen,
including pancreatitis.
Tell your doctor if you have
diabetic retinopathy
or vision changes.
Taking Ozempic® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may increase the risk
for low blood sugar.
Common side effects are nausea,
vomiting, diarrhea,
stomach pain, and constipation.
Some side effects
can lead to dehydration,
which may worsen
kidney problems.
I discovered the potential
with Ozempic®.
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh! Ozempic®! ♪♪
Ask your healthcare provider
if Ozempic® is right for you.
My experience with USAA
has been excellent.
They really appreciate
the military family
and it really shows.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
It was funny because
when we would call
another insurance company,
hey would say
“Oh we can't beat USAA”
We're the Webber family.
We're the Tenney's
We're the Hayles,
and we're USAA members for life.
♪
Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
Mom! He's Blinking too loud.
Sorry, is that too loud?
♪
You don't need any more hormones
in your house.
That's why you chose Kraft
Natural Cheese.
Made with fresh milk without the
added hormone rbST.
It's Cheese as it should be.
If you want to know why people
sacrifice everything for love,
you have to start by asking...
Could listening to Audible
help you find the secret
to a stronger relationship?
Sometimes it doesn't take
anything at all for us...
Just say "Alexa,
give me my free Audible book,"
and your first
pick is on us.
Gentle means everything.
So we improved everything.
We used 50% fewer ingredients.