>>> ALL RIGHT.
THAT WRAPS UP THIS HOUR OF MSNBC
LIVE.
MY FRIEND ALI VELSHI HERE TO
PICK UP OUR COVERAGE.
>> NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
FUN WORKING WITH YOU YESTERDAY,
COVERING A DIFFICULT STORY BUT
THANK YOU FOR YOUR COVERAGE.
>> ARE YOU DONE?
>> I AM DONE.
>> HAVE A GREAT REST OF THE DAY.
>> YOU TOO.
>> I'M ALI VELSHI, 2:00 IN THE
EAST WHERE A DEADLINE HAS JUST
PASSED WHERE THE WHITE HOUSE
WILL KEEP FIGHTING.
A FEDERAL JUDGE IN MARYLAND
OVERSEEING THREE SEPARATE
LAWSUITS OVER THE QUESTION RULES
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION MUST
EXPLAIN HOW IT'S GOING TO
PROCEED BY 2:00 P.M.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ADDRESSED THE
CONTROVERSY WITH REPORTERS
EARLIER.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO ISSUE AN
EXECUTIVE ORDER ON THE CENSUS?
>> IT'S ONE OF THE WAYS WE'RE
THINKING ABOUT DOING IT
SERIOUSLY, WE'RE DOING WELL ON
THE CENSUS.
>> [ INAUDIBLE ].
>> NO.
HE MADE A STATEMENT AND WROTE
SOMETHING OUT.
THE JUDGE DIDN'T LIKE IT.
I HAVE A LOT OF RESPECT FOR
JUSTICE ROBERTS BUT HE DIDN'T
LIKE IT, BUT HE DID SAY COME
BACK.
ESSENTIALLY HE SAID, COME BACK.
THAT'S WHAT HE WAS SAYING.
WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> THE CASE SEEMED ALL BUT
SETTLED A FEW DAYS AGO.
THE SUPREME COURT RULED LAST
WEEK THAT COMMERCE DEPARTMENT'S
CURRENT JUSTIFICATION FOR
PUTTING THE QUESTION ON THE
CENSUS WAS NOT LEGALLY SOUND
CALLING IT CONTRIVED.
THE GOVERNMENT HAS BEGUN
PRINTING COPIES WITHOUT THE
QUESTION INCLUDED.
THE PRESIDENT REPORTEDLY SPURRED
ON BY ALLIES ANNOUNCED ON
TWITTER HIS ADMINISTRATION WOULD
ONCE AGAIN TAKE UP THE FIGHT
SENDING WHITE HOUSE LAWYERS
SCRAMBLING TO COME UP WITH A NEW
ARGUMENT.
JOINING ME JUSTICE CORRESPONDENT
PETE WILLIAMS.
PETE, YOU HAVE HAD A LOT OF
SPECIFIC GUIDANCE THAT YOU'VE
BEEN GIVING US THROUGH THE
DAY --
>> PARDON, I'M GOING TO LOOK
AWAY, THIS IS GOING TO PANIC
EVERYONE TO SPEAKING TO ME IN MY
EAR, I'M LISTENING BUT LOOKING
AT SOMETHING THAT HAS BEEN
FILED.
>> THAT'S WHAT WE'RE WAITING
FOR.
2:00 P.M. DEADLINE FOR A FILING
IN WHICH THE GOVERNMENT EITHER
HAD TO SAY WE'RE GOING TO
CONTINUE ON WITH THIS FIGHT OR
IT COULD SAY WE'RE NOT
CONTINUING.
THE 2:00 P.M., THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING THAT WOULD
HAPPEN IF THE GOVERNMENT WOULD
SAY WE'RE GIVING IT UP.
THAT'S ESSENTIALLY WHAT WE'RE
WAITING FOR.
IF THE GOVERNMENT DOESN'T CHOOSE
TO WITHDRAW ITS FIGHT THEN
THINGS CONTINUE AS THEY ARE.
THE CENSUS WILL BE PRINTED, THE
GOVERNMENT WILL HAVE TO FIGURE
OUT A NEW WAY TO GET IT ON THERE
AND THAT MAY NOT HAPPEN.
>> THIS IS WHAT'S JUST A SECOND
AGO BEEN FILED BY THE GOVERNMENT
AND NO SURPRISE HERE, THEY SAY
WE'RE GOING TO KEEP FIGHTING.
THEY FILE WHAT THEY CALL THEIR
PROPOSED DISCOVERY PLAN AND WHAT
THEY SAY IS, THEY LAY OUT A
SCHEDULE FOR HOW TO CONTINUE IN
THIS MARYLAND LAWSUIT, A
SEPARATE LAWSUIT FROM THE
SUPREME COURTS CASE, ON THE
CENSUS FORM.
SO NO SURPRISE HERE, THE
GOVERNMENT SAYS IT WANTS TO
CONTINUE FIGHTING.
>> WHILE YOU READ THAT, THE
GOVERNMENT SAYS IT'S GOING TO
CONTINUE FIGHTING FOR THE MOMENT
THE GOVERNMENT CONTINUES TO
PRINT THE CENSUS FORMS BECAUSE
THAT WAS THE ARGUMENT THEY USED
THEY NEEDED A JUDGMENT OR AT
LEAST SOME KIND OF GUIDANCE FROM
THE SUPREME COURT BEFORE JUNE
30th IN ORDER TO PRINT THESE
FORMS.
SO THOSE FORMS CONTINUE TO BE
PRINTED.
THE GOVERNMENT IS NOT GIVING UP
ITS FIGHT.
LOGISTICALLY, PETE, WHAT HAPPENS
NEXT?
CAN THE -- WHAT CAN HAPPEN?
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO HERE ARE THE OPTIONS BASED ON
WHAT I HAVE JUST BEEN ABLE TO
READ FROM WHAT THE GOVERNMENT
HAS FILED AND THE OTHER SIDE IN
THE CASE HAS FILED.
SO FIRST WE HAVE THE SUPREME
COURT CASE.
THAT WAS STARTED FROM A LAWSUIT
FILED BY 18 STATES LED BY NEW
YORK, WENT TO THE U.S. SUPREME
COURT, LAST WEEK THE SUPREME
COURT SAID THIS EXPLANATION THAT
COMMERCE SECRETARY WILBUR ROSS
GAVE FOR WHY HE WANTED THE
QUESTION ON THE FORM CLEARLY
DOESN'T WASH.
YOU CAN'T PRINT THE CENSUS IF
THAT'S THE BASIS FOR WANTING IT
ON THE FORM.
THE SUPREME COURT HAS ORDERED
THE GOVERNMENT NOT TO PRINT THE
CENSUS WITH THAT QUESTION ON IT
AND, IN FACT, IT'S NOW PRINTING
IT WITHOUT THAT QUESTION.
SO WHAT ARE THE ALTERNATIVES.
ONE WILBUR ROSS COULD COME UP
WITH A NEW JUSTIFICATION FOR IT
THAT WOULD START A WHOLE NEW
ROUND OF LITIGATION.
THE GOVERNMENT CLEARLY THINKS
THAT'S NOT A PRODUCTIVE WAY
BECAUSE THEY THOUGHT EARLIER
THIS WEEK IT WAS OVER AND THE
PRESIDENT SAID YOU HAVE TO KEEP
TRYING.
ANOTHER POSSIBILITY THAT THE
PRESIDENT HIMSELF RAISED TODAY
IS, THE PRESIDENT SIMPLY SIGNS
AN EXECUTIVE ORDER DIRECTING THE
COMMERCE DEPARTMENT TO TELL THE
CENSUS BUREAU TO PUT THE
QUESTION ON THE FORM THAT WOULD
START A NEW ROUND OF LITIGATION.
ALL THESE -- ANYTHING THE
GOVERNMENT DOES FROM HERE ON
IS --
>> LET'S STOP FOR A SECOND.
EXECUTIVE ORDERS.
THIS PRESIDENT BELIEVES IN.
HE'S NOT THE FIRST PRESIDENT TO
THINK SO, THAT CERTAIN THINGS
CAN BE DONE BY EXECUTIVE ORDER
BUT IS THE PRESIDENT CLEAR AN
EXECUTIVE ORDER TO PUT THE
QUESTION ON THE CENSUS DOESN'T
MEAN THE CENSUS GETS PRINTED
WITH THE CITIZENSHIP QUESTION ON
IT?
>> CORRECT.
IT'S NOT GOING TO DO IT BY
ITSELF BECAUSE THAT WILL
IMMEDIATELY PRODUCE ANOTHER
COURT CHALLENGE.
ANYTHING THE GOVERNMENT DOES
FROM HERE ON IS GOING TO PRODUCE
A COURT CHALLENGE.
THAT'S A CERTAINTY.
SO BACK TO YOUR QUESTION USING
THE WORD LOGISTICS, HOW LONG
WOULD THAT TAKE?
HOW LONG DOES THE GOVERNMENT
HAVE BEFORE IT REALLY CAN'T --
IT HAS TO KEEP PRINTING THE
FORMS WITHOUT THE QUESTION.
I DON'T THINK ANYBODY HAS A
GOOD, CLEAR ANSWER TO WHEN THE
FINAL DROP DEAD DATE IS FOR NOT
TINKERING AROUND WITH THIS THING
ANY FURTHER.
IT'S GOINGS TO COST A LOT OF
MONEY IF THEY THROW AWAY ALL THE
FORMS THEY'VE ALREADY PRINTED
AND START OVER AGAIN.
ANOTHER OPTION, THOUGH, WOULD BE
TO EITHER INCLUDE THIS
CITIZENSHIP QUESTION ON THE
LONGER FORM, THE HOUSEHOLD
SURVEY THAT GOES TO A SMALL
PERSONAL OF U.S. HOUSEHOLDS, OR
AN ADDITIONAL FORM, AN
ADDITIONAL QUESTION THAT GOES
WITH THE SHORT FORM THAT GOES TO
ALL HOUSEHOLDS, JUST A SIMPLE
PIECE OF PAPER THAT SAYS ARE YOU
A U.S. CITIZEN, YES OR NO, WHAT
THEY WANTED TO PUT ON THE FORM
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THAT, TOO, WOULD LEAD TO
LITIGATION BECAUSE THE GROUPS
OPPOSED SAY WHITE HAVE IS THE
SAME KIND OF CHILLING EFFECT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, AS WE THINK
THROUGH ALL THIS, REMEMBER, NO
MATTER WHAT YOU MAY THINK OF
THIS AS A POLICY MATTER, OF
WHETHER IT'S A WISE THING TO PUT
THIS ON THE FORM, WHETHER IT
WILL LEAD TO AN UNDER COUNT OR
GIVE US MORE INFORMATION, THAT'S
A BALANCING TEST.
JUST RECALL THAT THROUGHOUT MOST
CENSUSES IN AMERICAN HISTORY
THERE HAS BEEN A CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION.
THE GOVERNMENT HAS SOME WEIGHT
ON ITS SIDE IF IT CAN COME UP
WITH A RATIONALE THAT SATISFIES
THESE CHALLENGES.
ONE OTHER POINT, THE PRESIDENT
SAID TODAY WHEN ASKED WHY DO YOU
WANT THIS QUESTION ON THE FORM,
YOU NEED IT TO FIGURE OUT HOW
MANY SEATS A STATE GETS IN THE
HOUSE.
THAT IS DEMONSTRABLY NOT TRUE.
NO APPORTIONMENT THROUGHOUT OUR
HISTORY, WE CELEBRATED ANOTHER
BIRTHDAY, HAS EVER BEEN BASED ON
JUST COUNTING CITIZENS.
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN TOTAL
INHABITANTS.
THAT WAS CLEAR FROM THE
CONSTITUTIONAL CONVENTION AND
WHEN CONGRESS ENACTED THE 14th
AMENDMENT WHICH GAVE FURTHER
GUIDANCE ON HOW TO CONDUCT A
CENSUS.
YOU DON'T NEED CITIZENSHIP TO
APPORTION THE HOUSE.
>> YOU CAN HANG OUT WITH ME
WHILE I BRING BARBARA McQUADE
IN, YOU HAVE READING TO DO, SO
YOU'RE WELCOME TO SIT IN FRONT
OF THE CAMERA AND IF YOU HEAR
SOMETHING YOU WANT CHIME IN.
BRING IN FORMER U.S. ATTORNEY
BARBARA McQUADE IN.
THERE'S A LOT TO GET THROUGH
HERE.
THIS SEEMED LIKE A SIMPLE
QUESTION AT ONE TIME, CAN YOU
PUT THE CITIZENSHIP QUESTION ON
THE CENSUS OR NOT.
NOW IT'S GOTTEN COMPLICATED
BECAUSE THE SUPREME COURT SAID
THAT THE COMMERCE DEPARTMENT'S
REASONING WAS NOT APPROPRIATE
FOR DOING SO, BUT THEY DIDN'T
SAY THAT MEANS TO PETE'S EARLIER
POINT THAT A CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION CAN'T BE ON THE CENSUS.
BASICALLY THE SUPREME COURT SAID
TO THE GOVERNMENT, YOU CAN COME
BACK WITH A BETTER REASON AND
TRY AGAIN.
>> WELL, THEY CAN, BUT IT HAS TO
BE A GENUINE REASON.
WHAT THE COURT FOUND WAS, THAT
THE REASON THAT THEY GAVE THAT
THE PURPOSE WAS SO THAT THEY
COULD BETTER COMPLY WITH THE
VOTING RIGHTS ACT, WAS A LIE, A
PRETEXT.
THE WORD THEY USED WAS
CONTRIVANCE.
IF YOU WANT TO TRY AGAIN AND
TELL US THE REAL REASON WE'LL
CONSIDER THAT.
IT'S HARD TO IMAGINE THEY COULD
SAY YOU KNOW, WHEN WE TOLD YOU
IT WAS ABOUT THE VOTING RIGHTS
ACT WE MADE A MISTAKE.
THE REAL REASON WAS THE
FOLLOWING.
IT'S HARD TO IMAGINE THAT ANY
NEW REASON THEY CAME UP WITH, MY
DOG ATE IT, IS SOMETHING THAT
COULD BE BELIEVED.
IT'S HARD TO IMAGINE GOING
FORWARD THAT THERE'S GOING TO BE
A PATH TO VICTORY HERE FOR
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> NOW THERE'S ANOTHER ISSUE AND
THAT IS THAT THESE -- THE
GOVERNMENT'S LAWYERS WENT TO THE
SUPREME COURT AND SAID, WE KIND
OF NEED THIS DONE IN A HURRY
BECAUSE WE HAVE TO PRINT THESE
FORMS BY JUNE 30th IN ORDER TO
GET THEM PRINTED AND DISTRIBUTED
ON TIME.
NOW, WHEN YOU GO BACK TO THE
SUPREME COURT AND YOU SAY YEAH,
THAT DEADLINE WE TOLD YOU WE
NEEDED IT DONE BY, BECAUSE WE
HAVE DIFFERENT REASONS WE CAN
PUSH THAT DEADLINE, DOES THAT
AFFECT THE CREDIBILITY OF THE
GOVERNMENT'S LAWYERS IN FRONT OF
THE SUPREME COURT OR IS THAT NOT
IMPORTANT?
>> NO, IT ABSOLUTELY DOES.
ERRY LAWYER WHO WORKS FOR THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE NOT ONLY
LIKE EVERY LAWYER DO THEY HAVE A
DUTY OF CANDOR TO THE TRIBUNAL
BUT THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT HAS A
HIGHER DUTY AS LAWYERS ON BEHALF
OF THE UNITED STATES TO TELL THE
TRUTH.
IN FACT, HERE IT WASN'T JUST A
PASSING STATEMENT THAT THEY MADE
THAT COULD BE CHARACTERIZED AS A
SLIP OF THE TONGUE, THEY
AFFIRMATIVELY SAID WE DON'T HAVE
TIME TO GO TO THE NORMAL ROUTE
OF THE SECOND CIRCUIT COURT OF
APPEALS BECAUSE TIME IS OF THE
ESSENCE AND THIS IS OF SUCH
PUBLIC IMPORTANCE WE NEED TO
SKIP THAT STEP AND GO TO THE
SUPREME COURT BECAUSE JUNE 30th
IS OUR DEADLINE FOR GETTING THIS
PRINTED.
TO GO BACK AND SAY WE MADE THAT
UP WOULD HARM THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT AND EVERY OTHER CASE
IT LITIGATES EVERY DAY AROUND
THE COUNTRY.
>> PETE?
>> JUST -- THIS IS A SHORT THING
THAT THE GOVERNMENT FILED HERE,
AND I DON'T THINK IT REALLY
CHANGES A LOT OF WHAT WE'VE
SAID.
TO AMPLIFY ONE THING, THEY SAY,
JUDGE WE'RE CURRENT ENJOINED IN
PRINTING A CENSUS QUESTIONNAIRE
THAT INCLUDES THE CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION.
WE'RE NOT DOING IT.
BUT ANY NEW DECISION BY THE
COMMERCE DEPARTMENT ON PROVIDING
ANOTHER RATIONALE FOR WHY IT
WANTS TO DO THIS WOULD
CONSTITUTE A NEW FINAL ACTION
AND PLAINTIFFS WILL BE ENTITLED
TO CHALLENGE THE DECISION.
THAT GOES BACK TO WHAT WE WERE
SAYING EARLIER, IF THE COMMERCE
SECRETARY SAYS HERE'S WHY I WANT
TO DO IT THAT WOULD LEAD TO
ANOTHER ROUND OF LITIGATION.
ALL THEY SAY IS IN THE EVENT THE
COMMERCE DEPARTMENT ADOPTS A NEW
RATIONALE, THE GOVERNMENT WILL
IMMEDIATELY NOTIFY THIS COURT,
THE JUDGE IN MARYLAND, SO IT CAN
DETERMINE WHETHER THERE'S ANY
NEED FOR FURTHER PROCEEDINGS OR
RELIEF.
THAT'S THE SEPARATE MARYLAND
CASE THAT DID NOT GO TO THE
SUPREME COURT THAT IS STILL
SIMMERING.
>> THANK YOU FOR YOUR GREAT
REPORTING ON THIS, PETE
WILLIAMS, AND BARBARA McQUAID,
THANK YOU AS ALWAYS.
BARBARA McQUADE IS A FORMER USE
ATTORNEY GENERAL FOR THE EASTERN
DISTRICT OF MICHIGAN.
PETE WILLIAMS OUR JUSTICE
REPORTER WILL CONTINUE TO REPORT
ON THIS.
>>> THE FIRST FRIDAY OF THE
MONTH IT MUST BE JOBS DAY AND
JUNE'S NUMBERS APPEAR TO BE A
CORRECTION FROM MAY'S DISMAL
SHOWING.
224,000 NET NEW JOBS WERE ADDED
LAST MONTH.
THAT'S A GOOD NUMBER.
DON'T LET ANYBODY TELL YOU
OTHERWISE.
UNEMPLOYMENT TICKED UP SLIGHTLY
FROM 3.6 TO 3.7%.
HOURLY EARNINGS UP 3.1% YEAR
OVER YEAR.
THAT LOOKS PRETTY GOOD.
REMEMBER, THAT YOU ALWAYS HAVE
TO SUBTRACT INFLATION FROM THAT.
ALL EYES ARE NOW ON THE FEDERAL
RESERVE WHERE CHAIRMAN JEROME
POWELL IS GOING TO HAVE TO
DECIDE WHETHER OR NOT THESE
NUMBERS WARRANT SLASHING
INTEREST RATES.
JOINING ME CNBC'S JOHN HARWOOD.
THIS IS A TOUGH ONE FOR THE
PRESIDENT TO SPIN BECAUSE ON ONE
HAND HE LIKES THE JOBS NUMBERS
ALMOST AS HE LIKES THE STOCK
MARKET NUMBERS.
THE TOUTING STRONG NUMBERS MEANS
THAT THE FED NOW HAS TO
RECONSIDER WHETHER OR NOT TO CUT
TRSZ, WHICH THE PRESIDENT REALLY
WANTS THE FED TO DO.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, ALI.
IT WON'T CONSTRAIN THE
PRESIDENT.
HE'S GOING TO CONTINUE TO WANT
THAT INTEREST RATE CUT BECAUSE
THE ECONOMY -- GROWTH IN THE
ECONOMY IS SLOWING FROM 2018 AND
HE WANTS IT TO REV UP AGAIN
GOING INTO THE 2020 ELECTION
YEAR.
BUT THE FED, WHICH WEIGHS DATA,
HAS GOT TO FIGURE OUT WHETHER OR
NOT THIS INDICATES THAT IT WOULD
BE TOO EARLY TO MAKE A RATE CUT
IN LIGHT OF THESE JOBS NUMBERS.
WE DID HAVE A DOWNWARD REVISION
ON APRIL AND JUNE, SO -- OR
EXCUSE ME, APRIL AND MAY, SO
THAT IS ONE NEGATIVE IN THAT
PICTURE, BUT NEVERTHELESS, THESE
ARE GOOD NUMBERS AND YOU KNOW,
JAY POWELL IN HIS LAST PRESS
CONFERENCE SAID THEY REMOVED THE
WORD PATIENCE FROM THEIR
GUIDANCE AND INDICATED THEY
WOULD BE INCLINED IF THE DATA
SUGGESTED TO CUT RATES ONE OR
MORE TIMES IN THE REST OF THE
YEAR.
THIS MAKES THAT DECISION MORE
DIFFICULT.
>> THE ONE THING THAT PRESIDENT
WANTS IS HE WANTS TO GOOSE THOSE
GROWTH NUMBERS.
THEY ARE A LITTLE SLOWER.
WE DO NOT APPEAR TO BE IN
RECESSION TERRITORY OR CLOSE TO
IT AT THIS POINT.
THEY ARE SMALLER THAN THEY WERE
AND THEY'RE SMALLER THAN THE
PRESIDENT HAD PROMISED WHEN HE
RAN IN HIS ELECTION.
IF YOU RECALL HE SAID MY
ECONOMISTS THINK IT WILL BE 3%,
I THINK IT COULD BE 4, 5, 6%.
THAT IS THE ONE LEVER THAT THE
GOVERNMENT HAS IN THEORY.
IF YOU INTEREST RATES IT'S LIKE
HITTING THE GAS PEDAL ON THE
ECONOMY, RIGHT.
THAT'S THE THING THAT CAN CAUSE
GROWTH TO INCREASE BECAUSE IT
BECOMES CHEAPER TO BORROW MONEY,
MONEY IS MORE AVAILABLE, PEOPLE
INVEST, THEY BUILD PLANTS, THEY
BUY HOUSES, THINGS LIKE THAT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S ALL THE MORE IMPORTANT FOR
HIM TO HIT THE GAS PEDAL SINCE
HIS OTHER FOOT IS HITTING THE
BRAKE WITH THE TRADE WAR.
THE UNCERTAINTY AND FRICTION
WITH CHINA, THE DISRUPTION OF
SUPPLY CHAINS, THE HIGHER
CONSUMER PRICES AS A RESULT,
POSE SOME RISKS TO THE ECONOMY.
IT'S NOT CLEAR WHETHER OR NOT IF
YOU CUT RATES, THAT THAT WOULD
WORK ON THE SAME TIME FRAME THAT
THE TRADE WAR IS DOING TO THE
ECONOMY, BUT THE FACT THAT HE'S
PULLED BACK A LITTLE BIT IF
RECENT DAYS FROM CONFLICT WITH
CHINA, THAT IN ITSELF IS GOOD
NEWS FOR THE ECONOMY AND THIS IS
ONE WAY HE CAN MAKE IT GO FASTER
IF JAY POWELL DECIDED TO GO
ALONG.
OF COURSE JAY POWELL IS
INDEPENDENT AND VALUES HIS
REPUTATION FOR INDEPENDENCE AND
WILL MAKE HIS OWN DECISION.
>> YOU HAD A CHANCE TO SIT DOWN
WITH BETO O'ROURKE AND TALK
ABOUT SOME OF HIS ECONOMIC
POLICIES.
>> LET ME ASK YOU ABOUT YOUR
EXPERIENCE AS A SMALL BUSINESS
MAN, BOTH WEB SERVICES COMPANY.
DO YOU LOOK UPON THAT AS A
SUCCESS AND WHAT DO YOU TAKE
FROM IT AS YOU THINK ABOUT THE
ECONOMIC CHALLENGES OF THE
COUNTRY?
>> YEAH.
SO I DO LOOK AT IT AS A SUCCESS,
TO BE ABLE WITH GOOD FRIENDS,
FAR MORE TALENTED AND SMARTER
THAN I WAS TO COME TOGETHER AND
CREATE OPPORTUNITY AND JOBS IN
THE THIRD POOREST URBAN COUNTY
IN THE UNITED STATES, HIGH
VALUE, HIGH SKILL, HIGH-TECH
JOBS IN EL PASO, TEXAS.
THAT FELT GOOD.
IT WAS HARD TO DO BUT I TELL YOU
I HAD SOME ADVANTAGES THAT OTHER
AMERICANS DON'T.
I GIVE YOU AN EXAMPLE.
I COULD NOT GET A LOAN IN 1998
TO START A TECHNOLOGY COMPANY IN
EL PASO.
JUST DIDN'T HAVE THE ASSETS THAT
THE BANK WOULD LEND AGAINST.
BUT MY DAD, WHO HAD A HOME THAT
WAS FULLY PAID FOR, COULD TAKE
OUT A LOAN ON HIS HOME AND THEN
LEND THAT MONEY BACK TO ME,
$20,000.
THAT WAS THE SEED CAPITAL THAT
ALLOWS TO START A BUSINESS THAT
ULTIMATELY HIRED DOZENS OF OUR
FELLOW EL PASOENS AND SERVED
CLIENTS ALL OVER THIS COUNTRY.
>> I OFTEN THINK THAT PEOPLE WHO
HAVE SMALL BUSINESS EXPERIENCE
COULD BE VERY USEFUL TO OUR
COUNTRY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO HAVE MACRO
ECONOMIC EXPERIENCE.
WHAT WAS YOUR TAKEAWAY.
YOU TALK TO PEOPLE ABOUT
BUSINESS AND ECONOMICS AND THEIR
UNDERSTANDING OF IT ALL THE
TIME.
>> THAT'S A SELLING POINT FOR
BETO O'ROURKE IN THIS RACE.
HE STARTED A BUSINESS AND IT'S
STILL GOING 20 YEARS LATER,
PROFITABLE BUSINESS THAT THE
PUBLISHING -- THE ALT WEEKLY HE
FOUNDED WENT OUT OF BUSINESS BUT
THE TECH SERVICES COMPANY,
THOUGH HE'S NO LONGER AN OWNER
OF IT, IS CONTINUING TO OPERATE.
THE POINT HE WENT ON TO MAKE IN
THAT DISCUSSION WAS THAT HE IS
MINDFUL THAT VERY FEW AMERICANS
HAVE FAMILIES THAT CAN STAKE
THEM TO $20,000 TO START A SMALL
BUSINESS.
A LOT OF HIS SMALL BUSINESS
PROPOSALS ARE DESIGNED TO EXTEND
MORE CREDIT, MORE TAX INCENTIVES
TO COMMUNITIES OF COLOR WHERE
WEALTH INEQUALITY HAS SUPPRESSED
THE FORMATION OF SMALL BUSINESS
AND THAT'S A BIG TALKING POINT
FOR HIM IN THE RACE.
>> I SKIPPED LUNCH, WHICH IS A
BAD IDEA, AND I KEPT WATCHING
YOU WHILE YOU WERE EATING AND
TRYING OUT WHAT YOU WERE EATING.
>> I WAS EATING THE ENCHILADA
PLATTER, HALF RED SAUCE, HALF
GREEN SAUCE.
IT WAS DELICIOUS.
HE HAD TACOS, AS YOU CAN SEE,
TALKING MOST OF THE TIME AND NOT
INCLINED TO PICK THEM UP.
>> I ENJOY INTERVIEWS WHERE
SOMEONE ELSE IS TALKING AND I'M
EATING.
THANK YOU, JOHN HARWOOD, EDITOR
AT LARGE AT CNBC.
>>> STILL TO COME THE PRESIDENT
ONCE AGAIN BLAMES THE BORDER
CRISIS ON DEMOCRATS SAYING
THEY'RE TREATING BORDER AGENTS
UNFAIRLY AND ACCUSED SOME
LAWMAKERS OF LYING.
REACTION FROM TEXAS DEMOCRAT
CONGRESSMAN MARK VESEY WHO
TOURED FACILITIES THIS WEEK.
JOE BIDEN ADMITS HE WAS
BLINDSIDED BY KAMALA HARRIS'
CONFRONTATION AT THE DEBATE.
DESPITE SLIDING POLLS HE SAYS
HE'S STILL THE BEST PICK TO TAKE
ON DONALD TRUMP.
LL THE BEST PICE
Going to the Shawn Mendes
Verizon UP concert
was like an
out of body experience.
We were right in front of him.
Dead center. Front row.
'Cause actually, Zarmina,
you touched Shawn Mendes.
Yeah, I touched him!
She touched Shawn Mendes!
He like held my hand
for a while.
And then we got
to meet him after,
which was like...
Another surprise.
Yeah.
We love Verizon even more now.
I'll never forget
that day. Ever.
(VO)
The network more people rely on,
gives you more.
Like thousands of tickets
to concerts,
festivals and private shows.
And big savings on
our best phones when you switch.
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
That's Verizon.
What do all these people
have in common, LiMu?
[ guttural grunt ]
Exactly. Nothing!
They're completely
different people.
That's why they
make customized
car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need.
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done it again, LiMu.
[ LiMu grunts ]
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
>>> ALL RIGHT.
AS THE DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES RACE TO QUALIFY FOR
THE NEXT DEBATE, WE'VE GOT NEW
FUNDRAISING NUMBERS TO REPORT.
MOMENTS AGO, SENATOR KAMALA
HARRIS' CAMPAIGN ANNOUNCED IT
RAISED NEARLY $12 MILLION IN THE
SECOND QUARTER.
STILL IN THE LEAD SOUTH BEND,
INDIANA, MAYOR PIECE BUTTIGIEG'S
CAMPAIGN ANNOUNCED MONDAY IT
RAISED $28.8 MILLION.
FRONT RUNNER BIDEN WITH $21.5
MILLION IN THE CORNER, STEVE
BULLOCK, WHO ONLY ENTERED IN MID
MAY AND MID-QUARTER RAISED A
SURPRISING $2 MILLION.
FORMER VICE PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN
ADDRESSING THOSE FIERY DEBATE
COMMENTS FROM 2020 OPPONENT
SENATOR KAMALA HARRIS
CRITICIZING HIS DECADES OLD
SENATE FIGHT AGAINST
DESEGREGATION OF BUSSING AND HIS
COMMENTS ON WORKING WITH
SEGREGATIONIST SENATORS.
IN A CNN INTERVIEW, BIDEN SAID
HARRIS' COMMENTS WERE
UNEXPECTED.
>> SO EASY TO GO BACK AND GO
BACK 30, 40, 50 YEARS AND TAKE
THE CONTEXT AND TAKE IT
COMPLETELY OUT OF CONTEXT.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, I GET ALL THIS
INFORMATION ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE'S
PAST AND WHAT THEY'VE DONE AND
NOT DONE AND, YOU KNOW, I'M NOT
GOING TO GO THERE.
>> BIDEN ALSO EXPRESSED HIS
CONFIDENCE IN DEFEATING
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
A NEW QUINNIPIAC UNIVERSITY
NATIONAL POLL SHOWS HIS 42% LEAD
IN THAT CATEGORY.
>> THE IDEA THAT I WOULD BE
INTIMIDATED BY DONALD TRUMP,
HE'S THE BULLY THAT I KNEW MY
WHOLE LIFE.
HE'S THE BULLY THAT I'VE ALWAYS
STOOD UP TO.
HE'S THE BULLY THAT USED TO MAKE
FUN WHEN I WAS A KID AND STUTTER
AND I WOULD SMACK IN THE MOUTH.
>> JOINING ME NOW IS POLITICAL
REPORTER JUST IN TIME FOR ALI V.
SEGMENT, ALI VITALI.
I WOULD BE ALI VELSHI.
TALK ABOUT HARRIS' CAMPAIGN
TALKING ABOUT WHAT JOE BIDEN
SAID, SAYING THIS WASN'T AN
ATTACK.
>> WELL, IT CLEARLY WAS AN
ATTACK AND I THINK THAT THEY
WERE DEFINITELY PREPARED FOR IT.
WE HAVE TALKED ABOUT IT BEFORE.
LILY ADAMS WAS ON CNN SAYING THE
FACT THAT HE WASN'T PREPARED FOR
IT, SHE'S NOT SURE WHY THAT
HAPPENED BUT THE KAMALA HARRIS
CAMP CAME IN AND THIS IS WHAT
DEBATES ARE TO SEPARATE THE
FIELD AND SHOW THE DIFFERENCES.
THERE'S A RETICENCE ON JOE
BIDEN'S PART TO BE APOLOGETIC
FOR HIS PAST RECORD AND IT'S
DIFFICULT TO RUN ON THE ARGUMENT
OF ELECTABILITY AND EXPERIENCE
WHEN YOU'RE NOT READY TO DEFEND
THE EXPERIENCE PORTION OF IT.
SPECIFICALLY, WHEN YOU LOOK AT
30 YEARS OF POLICY MAKING
DECISIONS, THINGS LOOK DIFFERENT
OVER THE COURSE OF TIME.
I COVERED A CANDIDATE WHO WAS
RETICENT TO APOLOGIZE IN THE
PAST, JOE BIDEN IS NOT DONALD
TRUMP, AND I THINK THIS IS A
STRATEGY I'M NOT SURE HOW
EFFECTIVE IT'S GOING TO BE GOING
DOWN THE LINE IN THIS CAMPAIGN
AS THERE ARE GOING TO BE MORE
POLICIES THAT COME UP ABOUT JOE
BIDEN'S PAST THAT THE OTHER
CANDIDATES WILL WANT TO
LITIGATE.
>> HARRIS IN THE POLLING WE WERE
SHOWING SEEMS TO BE CLOSING THE
GAP, HER NUMBERS HAVE SURGED 13
POINTS, JOE BIDEN'S HAVE SURGED
8 POINTS, BUT IN A DIFFERENT
QUESTION WHEN PEOPLE ARE ASKED,
WHO CAN BEAT DONALD TRUMP, JOE
BIDEN STILL WAY AHEAD.
I GUESS TO SOME DEGREE, KAMALA
HARRIS TAKING ON JOE BIDEN IN
THAT DEBATE WAS ABOUT SHOWING I
CAN BEAT A FRONTRUNNER?
>> MAYBE.
I THINK THAT FOR A LOT OF THE
CANDIDATES ON THAT STAGE WITH
JOE BIDEN, THE REASON WHY THE
CONVENTIONAL THINKING WAS IT'S A
GOOD THING TO SHARE THE DEBATE
STAGE WITH HIM BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY
A LOT OF EYES ARE LOOKING AT
HIM.
WHEN YOU'RE COMING INTO THIS
RACE AS JOE BIDEN OR BERNIE
SANDERS, YOU HAVE A HIGH NAME
RECOGNITION.
THAT'S WHY I THINK IN A LOT OF
EARLY POLLS YOU'RE SEEING THEM
SO FAR OUT AHEAD.
THEY HAVE LEADS NOW TO DEFEND.
FOR THE OTHER CANDIDATES IT'S A
MATTER OF INTRODUCING THEMSELVES
TO AN ELECTORATE THAT MAY NOT BE
AWARE OF THESE OTHER CANDIDATES
THAT ARE IN THE RACE NOW.
WHEN YOU SEE THESE POLLS
TIGHTENING, I ACTUALLY DON'T
KNOW THAT IT'S RISING LEVELS OF
SUPPORT AND NOT SUPPORT.
I ACTUALLY THINK IT'S JUST THE
ELECTORATE TUNING IN AND SHOWING
THAT THEY'RE BECOMING AWARE OF
DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
I THINK THAT AS WE GET FURTHER
DOWN THE LINE, WE'RE GOING TO
SEE A DEBATE IN JULY, A DEBATE
IN SEPTEMBER, THAT'S WHEN WE'RE
GOING TO START TO SEE A LOT MORE
OF THE AWARENESS COMING INTO THE
POLLS.
AFTER THAT I WOULD FEEL
COMFORTABLE LOOKING AT POLLS AND
SAYING THESE ARE TRENDS THAT ARE
STICKING.
>> THIS IS FOR US RIGHT NOW,
PEOPLE WHO WATCH THIS ALL THE
TIME.
>> EXACTLY.
>> OKAY.
MY EXECUTIVE PRODUCER INFORMS ME
YOU'RE ALI VIE TELE.
GOOD TO SEE YOU, MY FRIEND.
>> YOU TOO.
>> THEY WILL PAUSE THEIR FIGHT
OVER PAST EDUCATION POLICY TO
TALK ABOUT THE CURRENT STATE OF
AMERICA'S PUBLIC SCHOOLS.
THEY'RE SCHEDULED TO JOIN EIGHT
OTHER CANDIDATES AT THE NATIONAL
EDUCATION ASSOCIATION'S STRONG
PUBLIC SCHOOLS PRESIDENTIAL
FORUM IN HOUSTON.
THE CONTENDERS WILL ANSWER
QUESTIONS FROM CLASSROOM
TEACHERS AND OTHER EDUCATIONAL
PROFESSIONALS.
NBC'S -- MSNBC'S MARIANA JOINS
US FROM HOUSTON.
THE FORUM WILL BEGIN AT THE TOP
OF THE HOUR.
SOME OF THE CANDIDATES HAVE
OUTLINED PLANS TO IMPROVE THE
EDUCATION SYSTEM AND YOU'VE HAD
A CHANCE TO TALK WITH EDUCATORS
WHO WERE AT THE EVENT.
WHAT ARE THEY LOOKING FOR AND
WHAT ARE THE ATTENDEES LOOKING
FOR FROM THE PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES?
>> >> ALI, EDUCATORS WANT TO
KNOW FROM THE CANDIDATES HOW
THEY PLAN TO INCREASE TEACHER
PAY, FIRST OF ALL.
WE'VE SEEN TEACHERS FOR THE MOST
PART RALLY AND STRIKE ACROSS THE
COUNTRY FOR INCREASED TEACHER
PAY, BUT ALSO HOW THE CANDIDATES
WILL INCREASE FUNDING FOR
EDUCATION, HOW THEY'RE GOING TO
MAKE EDUCATORS STAY IN THE
CLASSROOM.
MANY TEACHERS HERE TELL ME THEY
HAVE TO WORK TWO, THREE JOBS
JUST TO BE AN EDUCATOR AND
HAVING TO PUT THEIR OWN MONEY
TOWARDS BUYING TEXTBOOKS AND
SCHOOL SUPPLIES.
HOW THE CANDIDATES WILL IMPROVE
CONDITIONS IN CLASSROOMS.
IT GOES BEYOND EDUCATION.
I SPOKE TO ONE TEACHER NAMED
CHRISTINA FROM DENVER, COLORADO,
WHO TELLS ME SHE HAS A CLASSROOM
OF MIXED STATUS KIDS, A LOT OF
LATINO FAMILIES, SO SHE'S ALSO
INTERESTED TO KNOW ABOUT THE
CANDIDATES' IMMIGRATION
PROPOSALS BECAUSE WHATEVER THEY
DO WILL INEVITABLY AFFECT THE
KIDS IN HER CLASSROOM.
FINALLY, WHAT YOU WERE TALKING
WITH ALI V., CHATTER HERE ABOUT
THAT CONTESTED EXCHANGE OVER
RACE BETWEEN BIDEN AND HARRIS.
A LOT OF EDUCATORS ALSO WANT TO
SEE WHAT BOTH OF OF THEM WILL
TALK ABOUT REGARDING THAT AT THE
FORUM TODAY.
ALI?
>> I APPRECIATE THAT.
THANK YOU.
WE'RE GOING TO CHECK IN WITH YOU
A LITTLE BIT LATER.
>>> A QUICK PROGRAMMING NOTE IN
THE NEXT HOUR I'M GOING TO BE
TALKING LIVE TO SENATOR AMY
KLOBUCHAR, ONE OF THE 2020
CONTENDERS ATTENDING TODAY'S
FORUM IN HOUSTON, GOING TO TALK
ABOUT HER PUBLIC EDUCATION
POLICIES, 3:00 P.M. EASTERN
RIGHT HERE ON MSNBC.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS I.C.E. AGENTS
WILL SOON BEGIN A NATIONWIDE
ROUNDUP OF UNDOCUMENTED
IMMIGRANTS AND CLAIM BORDER
FACILITIES ARE CLEAN, FINE AND
ONLY OVERCROWDED BECAUSE OF
DEMOCRATS.
TEXAS DEMOCRATIC CONGRESSMAN
MARC VEASEY WHO TOURED
FACILITIES, DETENTION
FACILITIES, JOINS ME NEXT.
YOU'RE WATCHING MSNBC.
children in urgent need.
It's not just about opening up
your home;
it is also about opening up
your heart.
Consider fostering.
-
(FLIGHT ATTENDANTS)
♪ When you have nausea,
heartburn, indigestion, upset
stomach, diarrhea. ♪
(VO)
Try New Pepto Liquicaps for fast
relief and ultra-coating.
(FLIGHT ATTENDANTS)
♪ Nausea, heartburn,
indigestion,
upset stomach, diarrhea. ♪
(VO)
Get powerful relief with new
Pepto Bismol Liquicaps.
This is your wake-up call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis,
month after month,
the clock is ticking on
irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
HUMIRA can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
HUMIRA targets and blocks a
source of inflammation
that contributes to joint pain
and irreversible damage.
HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections
including tuberculosis,
and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened;
as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor if
you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Help stop the clock
on further irreversible
joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here. Right now.
HUMIRA.
.
>>> I DON'T CALL THEM RAIDS.
I SAY THEY CAME IN ILLEGALLY AND
WE'RE BRINGING THEM OUT LEGALLY.
PEOPLE WHERE WE HAVE THE PAPERS,
HAVE GONE THROUGH THE COURT
SYSTEM AND THEY WILL BE STARTING
FAIRLY SOON.
I DON'T CALL THEM RAIDS.
THOUSANDS AND THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE WILL BE LEGALLY REMOVED
IN THE COUNTRY AND THAT PROCESS
HAS STARTED.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP ANNOUNCED HE
WOULD BE CARRYING OUT HIS
INITIATIVE TO ROUND UP AND MASS
DEPORT THOUSANDS OF UNDOCUMENTED
MIGRANTS TO THEIR HOME COUNTRIES
SOON TWO WEEKS AFTER HE CALLED
OFF THREAT AND RAID TS SEE IF
THE DEMOCRATS AND REPUBLICANS
CAN GET TOGETHER AND WORK OUT A
SOLUTION TO THE ASYLUM AND
LOOPHOLE PROBLEMS AT THE
SOUTHERN BORDER.
AT THE G-20 SUMMIT HE SAID
IMMIGRATION RAIDS WOULD LIKELY
TAKE PLACE SOME TIME AFTER THE
JULY 4th HOLIDAY.
IT COMES AS MORE REPORTS REVEAL
THAT ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN
SENDING HEFTY FINES OF UP TO
NEARLY $500,000 TO MIGRANTS WHO
SEEK REFUGE IN PLACES OF
WORSHIP.
JOINING ME IS MARC VEASEY WHO
TRAVELED TO EL PASO TO VISIT
SEVERAL DETENTION FACILITIES IN
THE AREA.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
>> ALI.
>> THE PRESIDENT HAS IMPLIED
THAT WHAT CONGRESSMEN ARE
SEEING, HOW DOES THAT COMPARE TO
WHAT OTHER MEMBERS OF CONGRESS
HAVE TOLD US AND OUR OWN
REPORTERS HAVE SEEN ABOUT
OVERCROWDING AND SHORTAGE OF
FOOD AND BLANKETS AND THINGS
LIKE THAT?
>> RIGHT.
EXACTLY.
I WAS ON THE TRIP TO EL PASO
SEVERAL DAYS AGO, AND WE VISITED
ONE OF THE DETENTION CENTERS
THERE THAT WAS UNDER A LOT OF
SCRUTINY AND WHAT WE SAW WAS, AT
LEAST ONE HOLDING CELL THAT WAS
CROWDED.
THEY HAD CUBAN MIGRANTS THAT
WERE PLACED IN THIS PARTICULAR
CELL AND THEY TOLD US THE REASON
THEY WERE IN SUCH AN OVERCROWDED
CELL BECAUSE THE CUBANS DIDN'T
MIX WELL WITH THE OTHER PEOPLE
FROM LATIN AMERICAN COUNTRIES
AND WANTED TO KEEP THEM TOGETHER
IN THE CELL.
THEY WERE CRYING, THEY WERE SAD.
ONE GRANDMOTHER TOLD A STORY OF
HER MENTALLY IMPAIRED GRANDSON
BEING SEPARATED FROM HER AND
THEY DID TELL MEMBERS OF THE
DELEGATION THAT WHEN THEY ASKED
FOR WATER, THAT THEY WERE TOLD
TO DRINK OUT OF THE TOILET.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU, BASED ON
THIS FACEBOOK PAGE THAT CAME OUT
AND THAT STORY ACTUALLY BROKE
WHILE WE WERE ON OUR TRIP TO EL
PASO, I BELIEVE THE BORDER
PATROL AGENTS DID TELL THEM.
I DO BELIEVE --
>> TELL ME THE CONNECTION
BETWEEN THE TWO.
YOU KNOW THAT THERE ARE ALMOST
10,000 PEOPLE ON THIS FACEBOOK
PAGE IN WHICH IT HAS CUSTOMS AND
BORDER PROTECTION EMPLOYEES AND
OFFICERS SAYING DISPARAGING,
SEXIST, RACIST, MISOGYNISTIC
THINGS ABOUT MEMBERS OF CONGRESS
AND MIGRANTS, ASYLUM SEEKERS,
EVEN PEOPLE CROSSING THE RIVER.
>> RIGHT.
YES.
I THINK IT'S A BROADER PART OF
THE CULTURE THERE AND NOW IT'S
BROKEN THEY HAVE KNOWN ABOUT
THIS PAGE PERHAPS FOR UP TO
THREE YEARS AND THIS WAS -- AND
THEY WERE NOT SURPRISED ABOUT
THIS.
WHEN WE GOT THERE AND TALKED
WITH THE CUSTOM AND BORDER
PATROL PEOPLE IN CHARGE OF OUR
TOUR THEY TOLD US OH, MY GOD,
WE'VE NEVER HEARD OF THIS.
COME ON, THREE YEARS.
IF THAT'S TRUE, THEN THAT MEANS
THAT WE WERE LIED TO, MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS WERE LIED TO ON THE
TRIP ABOUT THIS PAGE.
AGAIN, THE FACT THAT THEY WOULD
BE MEAN TO PEOPLE AND THAT THERE
WERE KIDS THAT WERE IN
OVERCROWDED CONDITIONS THAT WERE
WALKING AROUND WITH MUCUS FILLED
SHIRTS, STORIES TOLD TO US,
STORIES THAT IN MY OPINION WERE
BACKED UP BY THE I.G.'S REPORT
AND THE ACTING HOMELAND
SECRETARY SAID THE CONDITIONS
THERE ARE NOT GOOD.
I MEAN EVERYTHING THAT I'VE
HEARD FROM THE MIGRANTS WHEN I
WAS ON MY TRIP I 100% BELIEVE.
>> CONGRESSMAN, THE PRESIDENT
TALKED ABOUT IT THIS MORNING, HE
SAYS, MEMBERS OF CONGRESS ARE
ATTACKING BORDER PATROL.
LET'S LISTEN.
>> I'VE SEEN SOME OF THOSE
PLACES AND THEY ARE RUN
BEAUTIFULLY.
THEY'RE CLEAN.
THEY'RE GOOD.
THEY DO A GREAT JOB.
>> YOUR OWN GOVERNMENT --
>> THEY DO A GREAT JOB.
THEY'RE CROWDED BECAUSE THE
DEMOCRATS WILL NOT GIVE US ANY
RELIEF FROM THESE LOOPHOLES.
WE HAVE LOOPHOLES THAT ARE SO
BAD, WE HAVE ASYLUM THAT'S SO
BAD.
I THINK THAT THE BORDER PATROL
HAS BEEN TREATED VERY, VERY
BADLY BY CERTAIN MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS.
VERY, VERY BADLY.
FOR THE MOST PART THEY'RE VERY
RESPECTED BY CONGRESS BUT
CERTAIN MEMBERS OF CONGRESS SAY
VERY BAD THINGS AND LIE AND
EXAGGERATE.
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO SAY ABOUT
THAT, CONGRESSMAN?
HE'S SAYING THAT CERTAIN MEMBERS
OF CONGRESS LIE AND EXAGGERATE
BUT THIS WASN'T -- THIS BORDER
PATROL STUFF WASN'T ACTUALLY
REPORTED BY MEMBERS OF CONGRESS,
IT WAS REPORTED BY SOMEBODY IN
THAT GROUP WHO LEAKED IT TO
PROPUBLICA.
>> THAT IS ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
AND YOU KNOW, THE PRESIDENT HAS
NEVER SEEN A LIE THAT HE DIDN'T
LIKE.
AND RIGHT NOW HE'S JUST
SPINNING, HE'S PLAYING POLITICS
LIKE HE'S BEEN PLAYING POLITICS
WITH THESE MIGRANTS AND
ABSOLUTELY, ALI, EVERYTHING THAT
I'VE HEARD ABOUT AND EVERYTHING
THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS, YOU
KNOW -- ALMOST LIKE TRYING TO
PIT THE BORDER PATROL AGENTS AND
TRYING TO MAKE THIS A POLITICAL
ISSUE.
I WILL TELL YOU THAT THERE WAS
ANOTHER BORDER PATROL AGENT, YOU
MAY HAVE SAW THE INTERVIEW, AND
HE EVEN BACKED UP THE DEPLORABLE
CONDITIONS IN WHICH THE MIGRANTS
WERE LIVING IN.
SO I DON'T SEE THIS AS AN ISSUE
OF DEMOCRAT VERSUS BORDER PATROL
AGENTS.
I THINK THERE ARE SOME AGENTS
THERE THAT FEEL LIKE THEY ARE
EMPOWERED TO DO ANYTHING THEY
WANT TO DO BECAUSE OF THE
DIRECTION THAT THEY GET FROM THE
EXECUTIVE BRANCH, FROM THE
STATEMENTS THAT COME OUT OF THE
PRESIDENT'S MOUTH, FROM THE
ACTIONS THAT COME OUT OF THE
PRESIDENT'S IMMIGRATION POLICY
PEOPLE.
LIKE STEPHEN MILLER.
I THINK THAT SORT OF CULTURE HAS
BEEN ALLOWED TO EXIST THERE.
I BY NO MEANS THINK THAT EVERY
BORDER PATROL AGENT IS A BAD
PERSON.
WE EVEN HEARD FROM LAWYERS AND
OTHER PEOPLE BEFORE WE BEGAN OUR
TOUR IN EL PASO THAT WANTED TO
LET US KNOW SOME OF THESE BORDER
PATROL AGENTS ARE MEMBERS OF THE
COMMUNITY AND GOOD STANDING, WE
WORK WITH THEM, THAT THEY WERE
PART OF THEIR FAMILIES AND THAT
THEY CERTAINLY DID NOT PAINT
THEM WITH A BROAD BRUSH AND I'M
NOT TRYING TO DO THAT RIGHT NOW.
I'M SAYING THAT THEY HAVE A
PROBLEM THERE AND IT NEEDS TO BE
ROOTED OUT.
I'M VERY HAPPY ELIJAH CUMMINGS
IS GOING TO HEAR A HEARING ON
OVERSIGHT AND INVESTIGATION SO
WE CAN LOOK INTO SOME OF THESE
ALLEGATIONS WITH THE FACEBOOK
PAGE AND OVERCROWDED CONDITIONS.
>> THANK YOU FOR TAKING TIME TO
DISCUSS WITH US, REPRESENTATIVE
MARC VEASEY OF TEXAS.
>>> COMING UP NEXT, TENSIONS
WITH IRAN GO FROM BAD TO WORSE
AND THIS TIME IT'S TEHRAN AND
THE UK IN THE CROSS HEIRS AFTER
THE BRITISH ROYAL NAVY SEIZED AN
OIL TANKER.
YOU ARE WATCHING MSNBC.
SNBC
million.
There's everything from happy
To extremely happy.
There's also angry.
I'm really angry Clive!
Actually, really angry.
Thank you.
But what if your business could
understand
what your customers
are feeling...
and then do something about it.
Turn problems into
opportunities.
Thanks Drone.
Customers into fanatics
Change the whole experience.
Alright who wants to go again?
I do! I do!
I have a really good feeling
about this.
(ANNOUNCER)
IMPORTANT MESSAGE FOR WOMEN
AND MEN AGES 50 TO 85.
RIGHT NOW, IN AREAS LIKE YOURS,
PEOPLE HAVE ALREADY CALLED
ABOUT LIFE INSURANCE
THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM
AND RECEIVED THEIR FREE
BENEFICIARY PLANNER.
HAVE YOU RECEIVED
YOUR FREE PLANNER?
IF NOT, I ENCOURAGE YOU
TO PICK UP THE PHONE
AND TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THIS FREE OFFER.
IN ADDITION TO YOUR
FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
YOU'LL ALSO RECEIVE
FREE INFORMATION
ON AFFORDABLE
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE
THAT HAS A LIFETIME RATE LOCK
THAT GUARANTEES
YOUR RATE CAN NEVER INCREASE
FOR ANY REASON.
IF YOU DID NOT RECEIVE
YOUR FREE BENEFICIARY PLANNER,
CALL THIS NUMBER NOW.
PLEASE STAND BY TO LEARN MORE.
I'M ALEX TREBEK,
HERE TO TELL YOU ABOUT
A POPULAR LIFE INSURANCE PLAN
WITH A RATE LOCK
THAT LOCKS IN YOUR RATE FOR LIFE
SO IT CAN NEVER INCREASE.
DID YOU GET YOUR FREE
INFORMATION KIT?
IF NOT, PLEASE CALL
THIS NUMBER NOW.
THIS AFFORDABLE PLAN THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM
HAS COVERAGE OPTIONS
FOR JUST $9.95 A MONTH.
YOUR RATE IS LOCKED IN
AND CAN NEVER GO UP,
AND YOUR ACCEPTANCE
IS GUARANTEED
WITH NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
SEE HOW MUCH COVERAGE YOU CAN
GET FOR JUST $9.95 A MONTH.
CALL NOW FOR
YOUR FREE INFORMATION KIT.
>>> IRAN HAS THREATENED TO SOOEZ
AN OIL TANKER AFTER AUTHORITIES
DETAINED AN IRANIAN OIL TANKER
ON THURSDAY.
THE SHIP BREACHED EUROPEAN UNION
SANCTIONS CARRYING A SHIPMENT OF
CRUDE OIL TO SYRIA AND IRANIAN
AUTHORITIES BELIEVE THE BRITISH
WERE ACTING ON INTELLIGENCE FROM
THE UNITED STATES WHEN THEY
SEIZED THE SHIP.
IT COMES AS HASSAN ROUHANI SAID
HIS COUNTRY WILL BEGIN ENRICHING
URANIUM AS EARLY AS SUNDAY TO A
LEVEL THAT WOULD EXCEED THE
LEVEL SPECIFIED UNDER THE 2015
NUCLEAR ACCORD.
LET'S BRING IN BUREAU CHIEF ALI
ARUZI.
THIS IS A TRICKY ONE BECAUSE
MUCH OF THE SYRIAN REGIME
DESPISED AROUND THE WORLD AND
EVEN IN THE REGION IS SUPPORTED
BY THE IRANIANS SO IT WOULD BE
LOGICAL TO SOME PEOPLE TO THINK
THAT IRAN IS SUPPLYING OIL TO
SYRIA.
WHAT DO WE THOUGH ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED HERE?
>> WELL, ALI, WHAT WE KNOW IS
THAT THIS WAS IRAN SAID THEY
OWNED AND IT WAS TAKING CRUDE
OIL TO SYRIA, BUT IT WAS TAKING
A VERY CURIOUS ROUTE TO SYRIA.
INSTEAD OF GOING THROUGH THE
SUEZ CANAL, WHICH WOULD BE A
MASSIVE SHORTCUT FOR THIS
SUPERTANKER TO TAKE, IT WENT
AROUND THE TIP OF AFRICA ALL THE
WAY UP TOWARDS THE MEDITERRANEAN
COAST OF SYRIA WHERE IT WAS
SEIZED IN GIBRALTAR BY BRITISH
MARINES.
NOW IT'S VERY ODD THAT IT WOULD
TAKE THIS ROUTE.
SOME PEOPLE ARE SAYING THAT THIS
MAY BE A SMOKE SCREEN BY THE
IRANIANS TO DISGUISE ITS ROUTE
BECAUSE IT'S NOT ALLOWED TO TAKE
OIL FROM TO SYRIA BECAUSE OF EU
SANCTIONS AND THE BRITISH WERE
TIPPED OFF BY THE UNITED STATES
THAT THIS CARGO WAS HEADING TO
SYRIA.
SOME 30 BRITISH MARINES THEN
BOARDED THE SHIP, THEY BOARDED
IT BY ROPES COMING DOWN ON
HELICOPTERS, WHILE OTHERS CAME
ON SPEED BOATS, AND NOW THE SHIP
IS BEING HELD IN GIBRALTAR
WATERS.
THE CREW OF THE SHIP ARE BEING
QUESTIONED.
IT'S NOT CLEAR WHETHER THEY'RE
BEING QUESTIONED ON LAND OR ON
THE SEA.
INCIDENTALLY MOST OF THE CREW
ARE PAKISTANIS AND INDIANS, NOT
IRANIANS, THEY'RE NOT BEING
TREATED AS CRIMINALS BUT RATHER
AS WITNESSES.
NOW THE AUTHORITIES IN GIBRALTAR
HAVE SAID THEY ARE GOING TO KEEP
THE SHIP FOR ANOTHER TWO WEEKS
UNTIL THE INVESTIGATION COMES TO
AN END, BUT IRAN IS, OBVIOUSLY,
UP IN ARMS.
THEY ARE SAYING THAT THIS IS AN
ACT OF PIRACY BY THE BRITISH AND
AN IRANIAN COMMANDER
REVOLUTIONARY GUARD COMMANDER IS
SAYING THAT A BRITISH OIL TANKER
SHOULD BE SEIZED IN RETALIATION.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALI, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
NBC NEWS TEHRAN BUREAU CHIEF.
>>> THE SITUATION WITH IRAN IS
ONE OF THE CRISES THE PRESIDENT
IS DEALING WITH, TRYING TO REACH
AN AGREEMENT WITH CHINA TO END
THE TRADE WAR AND A DEAL WITH
NORTH KOREA TO CURB ITS NUCLEAR
PROGRAM WHILE DEMOCRATS AND SOME
REPUBLICANS HAVE CRITICIZED THE
PRESIDENT'S HANDLING OF FOREIGN
POLICY ISSUES, HIS CORE
SUPPORTERS STILL APPEAR TO BE ON
BOARD WITH HIS EFFORTS.
JOINING US TO TAKE A CLOSER LOOK
AT THIS IS HENRY OLSON, HENRY IS
A SENIOR FELLOW AT THE ETHICS
AND PUBLIC POLICY CENTER AND AN
OPINION COLUMNIST FOR THE
"WASHINGTON POST" AND WROTE A
COLUMN ON THIS ISSUE THAT WAS
PUBLISHED LAST WEEK.
HENRY, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME ON.
>> I WANT TO READ A LITTLE BIT
FROM THE COLUMN THAT YOU
PUBLISHED IN WHICH YOU SAY ABOUT
DONALD TRUMP, HIS FANS NOT
SURPRISINGLY TAKE A DIFFERENT
VIEW.
MOST DON'T SUBSCRIBE TO THE
TRUMP AS SUPERMAN FANTASY,
INSTEAD THEY RECOGNIZE THAT
EXPERTS HAVE BEEN IN CHARGE OF
U.S. FOREIGN POLICY FOR DECADES
AND THEY ARGUE WE HAVE LITTLE TO
SHOW FOR IT.
NORTH KOREA HAS NUCLEAR WEAPONS.
CHINA HAS EMERGED AS A DANGEROUS
GEOPOLITICAL FOE.
IN THEIR VIEW, TRUMP'S DRAMATIC
BREAKS WITH THE PAST COULD BE
THE ONLY CHANCE THE UNITED
STATES HAS TO AVERT DANGEROUS
CONFLICTS WITH ONE OR BOTH
NATIONS.
BETTER TO TAKE A CHANCE ON HIM,
THEY REASON, THAN HOPE MORE OF
THE SAME WILL YIELD DIFFERENT
RESULTS.
I THINK THAT'S A REMARKABLY
SOPHISTICATED VIEW OF WHAT MIGHT
BE HAPPENING.
DO YOU THINK THAT DONALD TRUMP'S
BASE HOLDS THAT VIEW OF HOW HE
HANDLES FOREIGN AFFAIRS?
>> I THINK THE PRESIDENT'S BASE
IS VERY SUPPORTIVE OF HIM.
THEY THINK HE HAS AMERICA'S BEST
INTEREST AT HEART.
THEY THINK HE'S NOT GOING TO BE
SOMEBODY WHO SECONDS AMERICAN
BOYS AND GIRLS TO DIE FOR AN
ALLY'S INTEREST THAT'S NOT
IMMEDIATELY IN AMERICA'S
INTERESTS AND I THINK THEY ARE
WILLING TO TAKE SOME PAIN OR
TAKE SOME RISKS IN ORDER TO
CONFRONT CHINA AN NORTH KOREA.
THE POLLS HAVE SHOWN FOR YEARS
THAT BEING CRITICAL TOWARDS
CHINA IS A WINNER, PARTICULARLY
IN THE MIDWEST, AND PARTICULARLY
WITH THE PEOPLE WHO MOVE FROM
DEMOCRATIC TO REPUBLICAN TO
SUPPORT PRESIDENT TRUMP.
SO I THINK THEY'RE SUPPORTIVE OF
HIM AND WILLING TO GIVE HIM A
LOT OF ROPE AND A LOT OF
OPPORTUNITIES TO SHOW THAT HE'S
DOING THE RIGHT THING?
>> IN BOTH OF THESE CASES A LOT
OF ROPE HAS BEEN CEDED.
IN CHINA WE'RE REPORTING ON
FARMERS WHO ARE SUFFERING
BECAUSE THEIR CROP PRICES ARE
LOW, GETTING SOME REIMBURSEMENTS
FROM THE GOVERNMENT, BUT EVERY
LAST FARMER WE TALKED TO SAID I
WOULD RATHER HAVE MONEY FROM MY
CROPS.
WHEN WE TALK TO THEM THEY SAY
WE'RE STILL STICKING BY THE
PRESIDENT.
WHEN DOES THAT RUN OUT, THAT
GOODWILL?
>> I THINK IT MAY NOT RUN OUT
VERY QUICKLY.
I THINK YOU'VE GOT PEOPLE WHO
RECOGNIZE THAT THIS HAS BEEN A
LONG TIME COMING.
CHINA EXCEEDED TO THE WTO ALMOST
20 YEARS AGO.
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE HAVE LOST
THEIR JOBS, ACCORDING TO M.I.T.
AND UNIVERSITY OF SAN DIEGO
ECONOMISTS BECAUSE OF CHINESE
IMPORT COMPETITION, AND FACT
THAT SOME FARMERS ARE LOSING
MONEY THEY CAN LOOK AROUND AND
SEE THAT THEIR NEIGHBORS LOST A
LOT MORE THAN THEY DID.
I THINK AS LONG AS THE PRESIDENT
IS FIRM AND AS LONG AS THE
PRESIDENT IS CONSISTENT, THAT
THE ROPE THEY GIVE HIM MAY BE
EXTENDED FOR QUITE A WHILE
LONGER.
>> I MEAN, THESE FARMERS LIVE ON
A RAZOR'S EDGE OF MARGINS.
ARE YOU SAYING IT MIGHT BE
ANOTHER YEAR OR TWO THAT THEY'LL
STICK BY THE PRESIDENT?
>> I THINK IT DEPENDS.
IT DEPENDS ON WHAT PRESIDENT
DOES.
THE THING TO REMEMBER IS THAT
THE FARMERS RECEIVE A LOT OF
GOVERNMENT SUPPORT.
THEY RECEIVE REVENUE SUPPORT,
THAT SOYBEAN FARMERS IN
PARTICULAR AND CORN FARMERS ARE
ABLE TO BUY INTO A GOVERNMENT
FINANCED INSURANCE PROGRAM THAT
GUARANTEES THEIR REVENUES.
PLUS THEY HAVE A PRICE SUPPORT
PROGRAM.
PLUS THEY HAVE A DISASTER
THIS IS A GROUP THAT MAY PREFER
TO SELL TO STEADY MARKETS BUT
THEY HAVE A LOT OF SUPPORT FROM
THE GOVERNMENT, PLUS THE
TEMPORARY SUPPORT THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAS BEEN ADDING TO SEE
THEM THROUGH OVER THE NEXT
COUPLE YEARS.
>> HENRY, GOOD TO TALK TO YOU
AND WE'LL CONTINUE THIS
CONVERSATION ANOTHER TIME.
HENRY OLSON IS VICE PRESIDENT
AND DIRECTOR AT THE NATIONAL
RESEARCH INITIATIVE.
>>> TODAY GOOD NEWS FROM THE
MONTHLY JOBS REPORT.
200,000 JOBS ARE ADDED, FURTHER
PROOF OUR ECONOMY IS STRONG, BUT
WHY DOESN'T IT SEEM TO BE
WORKING FOR EVERYONE?
THAT IS THE BIG QUESTION.
YOU'RE WATCHING MSNBC.
I have one kid in each branch
of the military,
but I'm command central.
It's so important to us
that Verizon
is supporting military families.
When I have a child deployed,
having a reliable network
means everything.
So, when I get a video chat,
and I get to see their face,
it's the best thing
in the world.
And I've earned every one
of these gray hairs.
Military moms, we serve too.
(VO)
The network more people rely on,
gives you more.
Like military plans with
a special price on Unlimited,
$100 per line, and big savings
on our best phones
when you switch.
That's Verizon.
When I book at Hilton.com
I get to select my room
from the floor plan...
Free Wi-Fi...
...and the Price
Match Guarantee.
So with Hilton
there is no catch.
Yeah the only catch
is I'm never leaving.
No I'm serious,
I live here now.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
LONGEST PERIOD OF ECONOMIC
EXPANSION ON RECORD.
BUT THERE IS A WIDENING GAP
BETWEEN THE RICHEST AMERICANS
AND EVERYONE ELSE.
MUCH OF THAT HAS TO DO WITH
WEALTH AND THE ABILITY FOR THE
MIDDLE CLASS OF AMERICA TO
ATTAIN IT.
LET'S JUST DISCUSS WHAT THIS IS.
WEALTHIER ASSETS, I THINK
EVERYONE KNOWS THIS, YOUR HOME,
YOUR DURABLE GOODS LIKE YOUR
TVs, YOUR REFRIGERATORS, ANY
STOCKS AND PENSION PLANS, IF YOU
OWN A BUSINESS.
ALL OF THAT MINUS YOUR
LIABILITIES THINGS LIKE YOUR
MORTGAGE, CREDIT CARD DEBT, CAR
PAYMENTS, THAT'S YOUR WEALTH,
YOUR ASSETS MINUS YOUR
LIABILITIES.
MORE THAN A THIRD OF GAINS IN
HOUSEHOLD WEALTH WENT TO THE
WEALTHIEST 1% OVER THE PAST
DECADE.
THIS ACTUALLY GOES ALL THE WAY
TO 1989, AND YOU CAN SEE THE TOP
1% HERE AND THE BOTTOM 50% HERE
WERE IN UNISON UNTIL THE
MID-90s.
REMEMBER THAT'S WHEN CHINA
JOINED THE WORLD TRADE
ORGANIZATION.
WE STARTED BUYING MORE STUFF
FROM THEM.
GLOBALIZATION AND TECHNOLOGY
TOOK HOLD.
THE TOP 1% ENDED UP WITH THESE
GAINS.
THE CHART SHOWS THE FOURTH
QUARTER TOTAL NET WORTH OF THE
TOP 1% OF WEALTH HOLDERS AND THE
BOTTOM 50%.
THESE FIGURES BY THE WAY ARE IN
MILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
AS YOU CAN SEE, THE BOTTOM 50%
BARELY, BARELY MAKING ANY GAINS
AT ALL.
IN FACT FOR A LITTLE WHILE HERE
IN THE 2000s, THEY WERE MAKING
NEGATIVE GAINS, THEY WERE LOSING
WEALTH.
SO WHAT'S CAUSING THIS DRAMATIC
DISPARITY?
THE "ASSOCIATED PRESS" ANALYZED
THAT FEWER MIDDLE CLASS
AMERICANS ARE OWNING HOMES.
THE PRICE GAINS IF YOU OWN A
HOME HAS MADE HOME OWNERSHIP
LESS FEASIBLE FOR NEW BUYERS.
SO IF YOU HAD A HOME, YOU'VE
DONE WELL.
IF YOU DIDN'T HAVE A HOME, THE
PRICES HAVE MADE IT HARD TO GET
IN.
BUT THEN THE RECESSION OCCURRED
AND NEARLY 8 MILLION AMERICANS
LOST THEIR HOMES.
SINCE THEN PRICES HAVE AGAIN
RISEN DRAMATICALLY IN PLACES
LIKE WEALTHY METRO AREAS,
ESPECIALLY ALONG THE COASTS.
IN 2004, MIDDLE-CLASS HOME
OWNERSHIP RATES STOOD AT ABOUT
70%.
IN 2016, WE ARE NOW AT ABOUT
60%.
SO THAT'S ONE AREA OF WEALTH.
THERE IS ALSO THE ISSUE OF LOW
PARTICIPATION IN THE STOCK
MARKET.
WE TALK A LOT ABOUT THE STOCK
THE PRESIDENT TALKS A LOT ABOUT
THE STOCK MARKET, BUT THE
PROPORTION OF MIDDLE-INCOME
HOUSEHOLDS THAT OWNS SHARES HAS
ACTUALLY DECLINED.
IN 200756% OF MIDDLE CLASS
AMERICANS OWNED SHARES.
AND BY THE WAY IN 2016, THAT
DROPPED TO 50%.
THIS DECLINE IS ATTRIBUTED TO
MORE MIDDLE-INCOME WORKERS
TAKING JOBS THAT DON'T HAVE
RETIREMENT SAVINGS PLANS AS WELL
AS EXPENSES LIKE HEALTH CARE AND
STUDENT LOAN DEBT WHICH ARE
TAKING THOSE BILLS, THAT MONEY,
THAT WOULD HAVE GONE TO
INVESTMENT.
NOW COMPARE THAT INVESTMENT RATE
TO THE TOP 10%.
ALMOST EVERYBODY IN THE TOP 10%
OWNS STOCK.
IN 2007 THE NUMBER WAS 93%.
IT IS UP TO THE 95% IN 2016.
SO THIS IS WEALTH DISPARITY.
JOINING ME NOW IS WASHINGTON
POST" ECONOMICS CORRESPONDENT
HEATHER LONG.
HER RECENT OP ED SPEAKS DIRECTLY
TO IISSUE.
AND, HEATHER, THE SIMPLE
QUESTION IS THAT IN SHORTHAND,
IF MAR TAKENS CAME DOWN TO EARTH
AND SAID HOW IS YOUR ECONOMY
DOING, THE SHORT ANSWER WOULD
HAVE TO BE GOOD.
ONLY IF THEY ASKED A SECOND
QUESTION WOULD YOU BE ABLE TO
SAY, BUT IT IS NOT EVENLY
DISTRIBUTED.
>> AS I TRAVELED THE COUNTRY,
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I HEAR.
AMERICAN LET'S TELL YOU THAT
THIS IS DEFINITELY A BETTER
ECONOMY THAN IT WAS IN 2008 AND
'09 DURING THE GREAT RECESSION.
BUT THE NEXT BUT OUT OF THEIR
MOUTH IS THEY STILL FEEL A LOT
OF ANXIETY.
AND IN OUR STORY TODAY WE CALL
IT 40% OF AMERICANS ARE STILL
STRUGGLING TO PAY THEIR BILLS
WHICH SEEMS LIKE A VERY
UNUSUALLY HIGH STATISTIC IN A
MOMENT WHEN WE HAVE SUCH A LOW
EMPLOYMENT RATE AND THE
PRESIDENT KEEPS TALKING ABOUT A
BLUE COLLAR JOBS BOOM.
SO WHY DO WE STILL HAVE THIS
BOTTOM 40% THAT'S STILL HURTING
SO MUCH?
AND THERE'S REALLY TWO PARTS TO
IT.
YOU JUST WALKED THROUGH THE
WEALTH SO WELL.
PEOPLE DON'T HAVE AS MUCH OF A
CUSHION AS THEY DID BEFORE.
WE HAVE HALF THE POPULATION THAT
HAS STILL NOT RECOVERED THE
LEVEL OF WEALTH THEY HAD JUST
BEFORE THE GREAT RECESSION.
SO THEY STILL DON'T HAVE AS MUCH
OF A CUSHION AS WHAT THEY WOULD
LIKE TO HAVE IN A NORMAL TIME,
LET ALONE HEADING INTO ANY
POTENTIAL DOWNTURN.
>> AND WE KNOW THAT
STATISTICALLY, BUT IN YOUR PIECE
YOU WROTE ABOUT THAT VERY
SPECIFICALLY.
IT SAYS IN DISCUSSIONS WITH 30
AMERICANS UNABLE TO PAY ALL OF
THEIR BILLS, A CLEAR PATTERN
EMERGED.
MOST WERE ABLE TO EEQ BY UNTIL
THEY FACED AN UNEXPECTED CRISIS
SUCH AS A JOB LOSS, CANCER, CAR
TROUBLE OR STORM DAMAGE OR IN
THE CASE OF THIS YEAR WE SAW
WITH GOVERNMENT EMPLOYEES WHO
WERE FURLOUGHED OR WHEN THE
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN.
THESE WERE MIDDLE-INCOME
WORKERS.
THESE WERE NOT POOR AMERICANS
BUT SOME SETBACK WILL SET THEM
OFF.
THAT MEANS THEY ARE CONSTANTLY
LIVING WITH A LEVEL OF ANXIETY
WHICH WOULD CAUSE THEM TO SAY
I'M NOT SURE WHOSE GREAT ECONOMY
YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT BECAUSE
I'M SCARED EVERY MONTH.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
I THINK WHAT WE'VE REALLY
LEARNED IN THE LAST DECADE ABOUT
PEOPLE WHO ARE IN THE WORKING
CLASS IS HOW VOLATILE THEIR
SITUATIONS ARE.
THERE'S A LOT LESS CERTAINTY
AROUND THE HOURS YOU'RE GOING TO
WORK AND HOW MUCH YOU'RE GOING
TO MAKE DURING THOSE HOURS.
RETAIL WORKERS HAVE TALKED A LOT
ABOUT HOW FRUSTRATED THEY ARE
ABOUT NOT KNOWING THEIR SCHEDULE
WEEK TO WEEK.
AND, YOU KNOW, ON THE FLIP SIDE
IS THAT PEOPLE NOT HAVING THAT
CUSHION ANYMORE.
THEY HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO SAVE.
THEY HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE AFTER
LOSING HOMES TO GET BACK ON THAT
HOUSING OR STOCK MARKET TO BUILD
BACK UP THEIR SAVINGS AND THEIR
ASSETS TO WEATHER A RAINY-DAY
SITUATION.
IT'S PRETTY STUNNING.
I THINK THE KAISER FOUNDATION
THAT GROUP THAT STUDIES HEALTH
CARE HAD A PRETTY INCREDIBLE
STATISTIC.
IT'S SOMETHING LIKE ONE IN SIX
AMERICANS EVEN IF THEY HAVE
HEALTH INSURANCE WILL FACE AN
UNEXPECTEDLY LARGE BILL THAT
THEY HADN'T PLANNED FOR EVERY
YEAR.
>> HEATHER, GOOD TO TALK TO YOU.
THANK YOU FOR THE STORY THAT
YOU'VE WRITTEN.
WE WILL CONTINUE TO HAVE THIS
CONVERSATION BECAUSE I THINK
IT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT ECONOMIC
CONVERSATION OF OUR TIME.
HEATHER LONG IS A WASHINGTON
POST" ECONOMICS CORRESPONDENT.
>>> ANOTHER QUICK REMINDER IN A
FEW MINUTES AT THE TOP OF THE
HOUR I'M GOING TO SPEAK LIVE TO
2020 CONTENDER SENATOR AMY
KLOBUCHAR.
STICK AROUND.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS THAT
CONVERSATION IN JUST A FEW
MINUTES.
YOU ARE WATCHING MSNBC.
Nothing feels like connecting
with the people that matter.
Holiday Inn.
Holiday Inn Express.
We're there.
So you can be too.
It all comes down
to a single defining moment...
...when a plan stops being a
plan and gets set into motion.
Today's Merrill
can help you get there
with the people, tools,
and personalized advice
to help turn your ambitions
into action.
What would you like
the power to do?
.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE THE LONGEST ECONOMIC
EXPANSION IN U.S. HISTORY IS
GOING TO CONTINUE, AT LEAST FOR
THE TIME BEING.
THE LABOR DEPARTMENT REPORTED
TODAY THAT HIRING REBOUNDED IN
JUNE WITH EMPLOYERS ADDING
224,000 NEW JOBS LAST MONTH.
THAT'S UP FROM JUST 72,000 IN
MAY, WHICH WAS A NOT VERY GOOD
NUMBER.
THE UNEMPLOYMENT RATE TICKED UP
TO 3.7%.
THAT'S A SIGN THAT MORE PEOPLE
ARE RETURNING TO THE WORKFORCE.
AND AVERAGE HOURLY EARNINGS WERE
UP JUST OVER 3% YEAR OVER YEAR.
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAILED THE NEWS.
>> WE HAD GREAT NUMBERS THIS
MORNING.
I THINK IT WAS 224,000 JOBS.
THOSE WERE REALLY UNEXPECTEDLY
GOOD.
AND OUR COUNTRY CONTINUES TO DO
REALLY WELL, REALLY, REALLY
WELL.
SO WE'RE VERY HAPPY ABOUT IT.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP MAY BE HAPPY
ABOUT THE NEWS.
THE MARKETS DON'T SEEM TO CARE
AS MUCH.
TAKING A LOOK AT THE BIG BOARD,
WE HAVE NOW AT LEAST MOVED TO
THE POINT WHERE WE ARE KIND OF
FLAT.
THE PROBLEM HERE OF COURSE IS
THAT A STRONG JOBS NUMBER MEANS
THAT THE FED MAY NOT LOWER
INTEREST RATES, WHICH IS
SOMETHING THE FED DOESN'T REALLY
WANT TO SEEM TO DO, BUT THE
PRESIDENT REALLY, REALLY WANTS
THE FED TO DO, AND THAT'S WHAT'S
TROUBLING INVESTORS.
BUT IT'S A HOLIDAY TRADING.
I WOULDN'T PUT TOO MUCH STOCK
INTO ANYTHING YOU SEE.
LET'S TAKE A CLOSER LOOK AT THIS
WITH MICHAEL.
HE IS THE DIRECTOR OF ECONOMIC
POLICY STUDIES AND A RESIDENT
SCHOLAR AT THE AMERICAN
ENTERPRISE INSTITUTE.
WE WOULD CALL HIM A CONSERVATIVE
ECONOMIST.
MICHAEL, GOOD TO SEE YOU, MY
FRIEND.
THIS IS A TRICKY SITUATION FOR
THE PRESIDENT BECAUSE HE LOVES A
STRONG STOCK MARKET, AND HE
LOVES LOW JOB NUMBERS, AND HE'S
GOT BOTH AT THE MOMENT.
BUT HE WANTS THE IF ED TO LOWER
INTEREST RATES AND DOES
SOMETHING LIKE THIS GIVE THE FED
PAUSE?
>> YEAH.
I THINK IT DOES GIVE THE
PEDESTRIAN PAUSE.
I THINK THERE HAS GENERALLY BEEN
A LOT OF HYPE ABOUT THE PATH OF
INTEREST RATES AMONG
COMMENTATORS AND ON WALL STREET
BEFORE TODAY'S JOB NUMBERS, YOU
KNOW, TALK OF A 50-BISCUIT OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I THINK THE FED, WELL, A LOT OF
THE CONCERN ABOUT SLOWNESS OF
THE ECONOMY WAS BASED ON WHAT WE
SAW IN LAST MONTH'S JOB NUMBER
WHEN IT WAS REPORTED THAT THE
ECONOMY ADDED 75,000 JOBS.
PEOPLE WERE CONCERNED THAT THAT
WAS A MARKET TURNING POINT, THAT
THE ECONOMY WAS SLOWING AND
PERHAPS SLOWING RAPIDLY AND THAT
THE FED NEEDED TO GET OUT AHEAD
OF THE ECONOMY AND KIND OF
CUSHION THE BLOW.
YOU KNOW, TODAY WE SEE A TOTALLY
DIFFERENT STORY.
AND I THINK PEOPLE OVERREACTED
TO LAST MONTH'S NEWS.
IT'S IMPORTANT NOT TO OVERREACT
TO THIS MONTH'S NEWS.
WHAT I THINK WE ARE SEEING IS AN
ECONOMY ADDING ABOUT 150 TO, YOU
KNOW, 180,000 JOBS A MONTH,
SLOWER THAN IN 2018.
BUT STILL SOLID AND STILL
STEADY.
>> YOU WROTE AN OP ED FOR THE
GUARDIAN NEWSPAPER IN WHICH YOU
TALKED ABOUT THE ECONOMY BEING
IN AS GOOD A SHAPE AS THE
ECONOMY SUGGESTS.
IT'S A STRANGE CONVERSATION TO
HAVE ABOUT WHETHER CAPITALISM IS
BROKEN.
THE REMARKABLE WEALTH IN THE
UNITED STATES AND BASICALLY
AROUND THE WORLD IS WHAT'S
MAKING PEOPLE SAY, HEY, I SEE
THAT THAT STOCK MARKET GOING UP
ALL THE TIME, I SEE HOME PRICES
GOING UP ALL THE TIME.
I SEE THIS STRONG ECONOMY, BUT
MY WAGES PARTICULARLY FOR SOME,
MAYBE IT'S ABOUT A THIRD OF
AMERICANS THEY FEEL LEFT OUT OF
THIS WHOLE THING, ABOUT A
SIMILAR PERCENTAGE OF PEOPLE IN
THE UNITED KINGDOM FEEL LEFT OUT
OF IT, PEOPLE IN FRANCE, PEOPLE
IN GERMANY.
THE ARAB SPRING STARTED WITH
SOMETHING SIMILAR.
PEOPLE SAID I'M DOING WHAT I'M
SUPPOSED TO DO BUT I'M NOT
RECOOPING THE FRUITS.
>> IF YOU LOOK FROM, SAY, 1980
UNTIL SAY THE GREAT RECESSION,
YOU SEE A SIGNIFICANT INCREASE
IN INEQUALITY.
IF YOU LOOK OVER THE LAST TEN
YEARS INEQUALITY GROWTH HAS
ACTUALLY FLATTENED AND IT MAY
HAVE EVEN DECLINED DEPENDING ON
WHICH INCOME MEASURE YOU'RE
INTERESTED IN.
AT THE SAME TIME AS INEQUALITY
WAS SOARING DURING THE 1990s,
PEOPLE WEREN'T CONCERNED ABOUT
INEQUALITY.
YOU KNOW, SO I THINK PEOPLE
ACTUALLY CARE ABOUT HOW THEY ARE
DOING.
>> RIGHT, RIGHT.
SO IN THE '90s.
SO ONE OF THE DIFFERENCES WAS IF
EVERYBODY'S SORT OF GOING UP AT
A LEVEL, I DON'T KNOW IF MY
CONTROL ROOM HAS THE SAME
NUMBERS THAT I PUT UP WITH
HEATHER LONG SINCE THE '80s AND
THE '90s.
WHEN YOU'VE GOT RELATIVE
FLATNESS AND EVEN DECLINE
AMONGST THE BOTTOM 50% THAT,
DOESN'T FEEL LIKE YOU'RE DOING
BETTER.
>> YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
AND WHEN WE HAD THIS MASSIVE
FINANCIAL CRISIS, THIS SERIOUS
RECESSION, AND THEN WE HAD A
RECOVERY THAT WAS SLOW.
THAT'S TYPICAL FOLLOWING
RECESSIONS AS SEVERE AS THIS
ONE.
BUT FOR YEARS AND YEARS AND
YEARS, WE HAD SLOW AND
NONACCELERATING WAGE GROWTH.
AND OVER THE LAST FEW YEARS,
THAT'S CHANGED THANK GOODNESS.
AND MY SENSE IS THAT IF WE HAVE
A LONG ENOUGH PERIOD WHERE WAGES
FOR TYPICAL WORKERS ARE GROWING
AT A DECENT CLIP, THAT SOME OF
THIS CONCERN THAT WE'RE SEEING
WILL DIE DOWN.
>> I HEAR YOUR ARGUMENT.
ARE YOU WORRIED THAT GIVEN HOW
LONG WE'RE INTO THIS EXPANSION
THAT JUST BY NATURAL CAUSES IT
WILL SLOW DOWN AND WE WON'T GET
THAT CONTINUED WAGE GROWTH?
BECAUSE IT'S ONLY REALLY SINCE
ABOUT 2015 THAT WE'VE SEEN A
NICE BUMP.
WE'VE SEEN SOME OF THAT EXTRA
CAPACITY IN THE LABOR MARKET GO
AWAY, AND PEOPLE ARE ACTUALLY
GETTING RAISES.
>> YEAH.
I AM WORRIED ABOUT THAT.
AND THAT ACTUALLY TIES IN NICELY
WITH WHAT WE LEARNED THIS
MORNING.
YOU KNOW, AGAIN, A SOLID MONTH,
BUT IT SEEMS CLEAR THAT 2019 IS
GOING TO BE A SLOWER YEAR FOR
THE LABOR MARKET THAN 2018.
YOU KNOW, ONE OF THE REASONS IS
BECAUSE WE'RE JUST RUNNING OUT
OF WORKERS TO BRING IN OFF THE
SIDELINES.
WE SAW THE LABOR FORCE
PARTICIPATION RATE TICK UP THIS
MONTH.
THAT'S FANTASTIC.
BUT THERE'S REALLY ONLY SO HIGH
THAT CAN GO.
THERE ARE ONLY SO MANY WORKERS
WE CAN BRING BACK IN.
AND AT SOME POINT WE ARE GOING
TO HAVE ANOTHER RECESSION.
AND SO I THINK YOUR QUESTION IS
A GOOD ONE.
HOW LONG CAN WE KEEP SOLID WAGE
GAINS GOING, AND IF THE ANSWER
IS NOT THAT MUCH LONGER, THEN
WHAT DOES THAT DO TO KIND OF
POLITICS AND WHAT DOES THAT DO
TO POPULAR SENTIMENT?
I THINK THAT'S A RATHER
IMPORTANT QUESTION WE ARE
FACING.
>> MICHAEL, I ALWAYS ENJOY
TALKING TO YOU.
THANK YOU FOR MAKING TIME FOR US
TODAY.
>>> AND ONCE AGAIN REMAINS
UNCLEAR IF THE 2020 CENSUS WILL
INCLUDE A CITIZENSHIP QUESTION.
JUST LAST HOUR, JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT LAWYERS TOLD A
FEDERAL COURT IN MARYLAND THAT
THEY WILL CONTINUE TO LOOK FOR
WAYS TO GET THE QUESTION ON THE
CENSUS DESPITE AN UNFAVORABLE
RULING FROM THE SUPREME COURT.
AND THE PRESIDENT REAFFIRMED HIS
COMMITMENT TO INCLUDING THE
QUESTION ON THE CENSUS EARLIER
TODAY MAYBE BY USING AN
EXECUTIVE ORDER.
>> I JUST SPOKE WITH THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL.
WE HAVE A NUMBER OF DIFFERENT
AVENUES.
WE COULD USE ALL OF THEM OR ONE.
WE ARE DOING VERY WELL ON THAT
ISSUE.
WE ARE SPENDING 15 TO
$20 BILLION ON A CENSUS.
WE ARE DOING EVERYTHING.
WE ARE FINDING OUT EVERYTHING
ABOUT EVERYBODY.
THINK OF IT.
15 TO $20 BILLION AND YOU'RE NOT
ALLOWED TO ASK THEM ARE YOU A
CITIZEN.
AND BY THE WAY IF YOU LOOK AT
THE HISTORY OF OUR COUNTRY, IT'S
ALMOST ALWAYS BEEN ASKED.
SO WE ARE FIGHTING VERY HARD
AGAINST THE SYSTEM THAT'S A VERY
DIFFICULT SYSTEM, BUT WE'LL MAKE
A DECISION.
>> JOINING ME NOW IS NBC NEWS
JUSTICE CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS.
THAT WAS A MOMENT OF
SELF-AWARENESS FOR THE
PRESIDENT.
HE SAID WE ARE FIGHTING IN A
SYSTEM AND IT'S A VERY DIFFICULT
SYSTEM.
IT IS COMPLEX AND IT IS
DIFFICULT.
THE PRESIDENT CAN'T ACTUALLY
JUST SAY PUT THE QUESTION ON
NOW.
>> WELL, HE CAN, BUT WHETHER
THAT WILL MAKE A DIFFERENCE
REMAINS TO BE SEEN.
I THINK AT THIS POINT ANYTHING
THE ADMINISTRATION DOES FROM
HERE ON IS GOING TO INVITE
LITIGATION AND THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT ADMITTED AS SUCH OR
CONCEDED THE POINT TODAY IN ITS
FILING WHAT THIS IS IN MARYLAND,
THIS IS A SEPARATE CASE, THIS IS
NOT THE ONE THAT WENT TO THE
SUPREME COURT.
IT'S ONE THAT IS STILL GOING ON
IN WHICH CHALLENGERS SAY ADDING
THIS QUESTION WOULD BE UNFAIR
DISCRIMINATION VIOLATING LEGAL
PROTECTION CLAUSE OF THE
CONSTITUTION.
AND WHAT THE GOVERNMENT SAYS IN
THE FILING BEFORE THAT JUDGE IS
THAT THEY'VE BEEN ASKED TO
RE-EVALUATE ALL AVAILABLE
OPTIONS THAT WOULD ALLOW FOR
PUTTING THIS QUESTION BACK ON
THE CENSUS FORM.
NO GREAT SURPRISE THERE GIVEN
WHAT THE PRESIDENT HAD SAID THIS
MORNING.
BUT THEY DO SAY THAT IF, FOR
EXAMPLE, COMMERCE SECRETARY ROSS
COMES UP WITH A NEW EXPLANATION
FOR WANTING TO PUT THIS QUESTION
ON THE FORM, THEN THE
PLAINTIFFS, THE PEOPLE WHO HAVE
CHALLENGED THAT, WILL BE FULLY
ENTITLED TO CHALLENGE THE
DECISION AT THAT TIME.
SO THEY CAN SEE THAT ALMOST
ANYTHING THEY DO AT THIS POINT
WILL BE PRODUCING A NEW LAWSUIT.
AND OF COURSE THE ISSUE THERE IS
IT PUTS ADDITIONAL PRESSURE ON
THE CENSUS BUREAU THE LONGER
THESE LAWSUITS PLAY OUT IN
COURT, THE LESS TIME THE CENSUS
BUREAU HAS TO GET THESE FORMS
PRINTED.
THIS LETTER DOES SAY DESPITE ALL
OF THIS BACK AND FORTH, NO
CENSUS FORMS ARE BEING PRINTED
NOW THAT HAVE THE CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION ON THEM.
THEY SAY THEY ARE CURRENTLY
ENJOINED BY ALL THESE COURT
RULINGS FROM PUTTING THE
QUESTIONNAIRE -- PUTTING THE
CENSUS QUESTIONNAIRE, PRINTING
RATHER A CENSUS QUESTIONNAIRE
THAT INCLUDES THIS CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION.
SO THEY ARE STILL TRYING TO FIND
SOME WAY TO DO IT, BUT JUST
ABOUT ANYTHING THEY TRY TO DO IS
UNDOUBTEDLY GOING TO PRODUCE
ANOTHER LAWSUIT, MORE
LITIGATION, AND MORE DELAY.
>> FOR TIME AND LOGISTICS
PURPOSES, UNDER WHAT CONSTRAINTS
IS THE CENSUS BUREAU OPERATING?
IN OTHER WORDS THE PRESIDENT
TALKED ABOUT DELAYING THE
CENSUS.
IS THAT ANOTHER COURT CASE OR
CAN THE PRESIDENT ACTUALLY DO
THAT?
>> AH.
WELL, TWO THINGS.
WHEN HE TALKED ABOUT DLACHLG THE
CENSUS, MY SENSE IS THAT HE
DIDN'T REALLY MEAN PUTTING OFF
WHEN THE DOORS GET KNOCKED ON
AND WHEN PEOPLE FILL OUT THE
FORM.
TRADITIONALLY THE CENSUS HAS
BEEN A SNAPSHOT OF WHO'S WHERE
ON APRIL 1st OF EVERY, YOU KNOW,
EVERY YEAR THAT ENDS IN A ZERO.
AND I CAN'T IMAGINE THAT THAT
WILL BE DELAYED.
WHAT I THINK -- WHAT I SUSPECT
HE WAS TALKING ABOUT IS GETTING
THE FORMS PRINTED.
BUT THE GOVERNMENT HAS SAID WE
HAVE TO START PRINTING THESE
THINGS JULY 1st.
AND INDEED THEY DID TO GET THEM
ALL DONE IN TIME.
IT RAISES A QUESTION THOUGH.
IF THEY HAVE TO START OVER, IF
THEY SOMEHOW PREVAIL AND ARE
ABLE TO ADD THIS QUESTION, COULD
THEY TRASH ALL THE STUFF THEY
HAVE PRINTED SO FAR AND START
OVER?
WOULD THEY HAVE ENOUGH TIME?
AND I GUESS THE ANSWER IS IF
THEY HAD ENOUGH MONEY, YES,
THEY'D JUST GET MORE PRINTERS
INVOLVED AND COULD PROBABLY GET
IT DONE.
I'M JUST NOT SURE WHERE THAT
MONEY COMES FROM, WHETHER THEY'D
HAVE TO GO BACK TO CONGRESS, AND
THAT WOULD ADD ANOTHER BIT OF
DELAY.
>> PETE WILLIAMS, NEVER BEEN
STUMPED BY A COMPLICATED
QUESTION.
>> I PRETEND NOT TO BE.
>> WITH ME NOW WASHINGTON POST"
OPINION WRITER JENNIFER REUBEN.
AND SHE'S A CONSERVATIVE AND SHE
WRITES IN A NEW HEADLINE CENSUS,
A FLAT-OUT WIN FOR PROGRESSIVES,
THE COURTS, AND AMERICA.
TELL ME ABOUT THAT, JENNIFER.
WHY DO YOU ADD PROGRESSIVES IN
THAT TITLE?
WHY DO YOU THINK IT'S A WIN FOR
PROGRESSIVES?
>> I THINK IT'S A WIN FOR
EVERYONE.
I THINK THE PROGRESSIVE GROUPS
THAT WERE LITIGANTING, GROUPS
LIKE THE ACLU WERE MAKING THE
VERY COGENT ARGUMENT THAT THE
PRESIDENT WAS INCLUDING THIS
QUESTION AS A WAY OF DETERRING
PEOPLE WHO MIGHT BE AFRAID TO
GIVE OUT THEIR INFORMATION OR
THE INFORMATION OF PEOPLE LIVING
WITH THEM REGARDING THEIR
IMMIGRANT STATUS.
AND THAT THIS IS ACTUALLY
CONTRARY TO LAW.
IT'S BEEN DECIDED A WHILE BACK
THAT THE CENSUS IS SUPPOSED TO
BE CATCHING EVERYBODY.
AND BY INCLUDING THIS QUESTION,
YOU'RE PURPOSEFULLY DIMINISHING
THE COUNT IN AREAS THAT THERE
PROBABLY ARE GOING TO BE SOME
BLUE REPRESENTATIVES, URBAN
AREAS, FOR EXAMPLE.
SO, I THINK FOR THEM THIS WAS A
LEGAL VICTORY AT THE SUPREME
COURT.
AND NOW THE PRESIDENT IS KIND OF
PLAYING WITH WORDS AND THE POOR
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT LAWYERS HAVE
HAVING TO GO INTO PORT TO MAKE
THEMSELVES LOOK AWFULLY FOOLISH.
UNDERSTAND WHAT THEY'VE SAID.
THEY HAVE SAID, WELL, WE DON'T
HAVE THE REAL REASON, WE DON'T
HAVE THE REAL NONPROTECTURAL
REASON YET.
BUT GIVE US A FEW REASONS AND WE
WILL COME UP WITH A REASON.
THEY ARE OBVIOUSLY JUST LOOKING
FOR ANOTHER LIE.
AND TO MAKE MATTERS WORSE, THE
MARILYN CASE IS THE CASE IN
WHICH SOME NEW EVIDENCE HAS COME
TO LIGHT.
THIS IS DAMNING TO THE
ADMINISTRATION.
APPARENTLY A COMPUTER FILE WAS
FOUND IN ORDER TO BENEFIT THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY BY
OVERCOUNTERING OR, IF YOU WILL,
TIPPING THE SCALES TOWARDS THE
WHITE POPULATION.
THIS IS COMPLETELY ILLEGAL.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT THE
PLAINTIFFS HAVE BEEN FEARING.
AND IF THEY WANT TO GO FORWARD,
THE PLAINTIFFS ARE SAYING, WELL,
YES, LET'S GO FORWARD, LET'S
COVER ALL OF THIS NEW
INFORMATION.
THE GOVERNMENT FILING TODAY
UNBELIEVABLY SAID GIVE US SOME
MORE TIME TO THINK OF A REASON,
BUT DON'T LET THEM LOOK AT THE
DISCOVERY.
>> WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE CONCEPT
OF A CENSUS, IT'S IN THE OLD
TESTAMENT, RIGHT?
>> RIGHT.
>> IT HAS BEEN HISTORICALLY
STOOD THAT IF YOU DON'T COUNT
PROPERLY, YOU MESS UP ON THE
PROVISIONS.
SHOULD THIS EVEN BE PARTISAN?
SHOULDN'T WE JUST ALL AGREE, AND
SOMETIMES IT'S GOING TO BENEFIT
CONSERVATIVES AND SOMETIMES IT'S
GOING TO BENEFIT PROGRESSIVES,
BUT SHOULDN'T WE JUST ALL BE
COUNTING PROPERLY AND NOT BE
DEBATING THIS?
>> WE SHOULD, BUT UNFORTUNATELY
THE PRESIDENT HAS MADE IT
PARTISAN.
HE IS DETERMINED NOT TO COUNT
EVERYBODY OR TO SET UP A
QUESTION THAT IS DESIGNED TO
MAKE A COUNT REALLY INACCURATE.
HE'S THE ONLY PRESIDENT THAT HAS
DONE THIS.
HE'S THE ONLY PRESIDENT WHO HAS
TAKEN OBJECTIVELY NEUTRAL THINGS
THAT SHOULD BE A MATTER OF
NONPARTISAN BEFORE THE FOURTH OF
JULY.
>> JUB OBJECTIVELY NEUTRAL.
>> IT SHOULD BE BUT NOT UNDER
THIS PRESIDENT.
HE WAS THE ONE WHO CAME UP WITH
THE IDEA, THE SECRETARY OF
COMMERCE WAS THE ONE WHO CAME UP
WITH A FALSE REASON, THE CHIEF
JUSTICE WAS VERY NICE NOT
CALLING HIM A LIAR, BUT HE
ESSENTIALLY SAID THE REASON
DOESN'T MATCH THE FACTS.
THAT'S LYING IN MY BOOK.
BUT HE SENT THEM BACK TO FIGURE
THIS WHOLE THING OUT I THINK
HOPING THAT IT WOULDN'T COME
BACK.
I SUSPECT IF IT EVER COMES BACK
TO THE SUPREME COURT, THE
SUPREME COURT WILL HAVE USED UP
THEIR PATIENCE ON THIS, AND WILL
SWAT IT AWAY AGAIN.
>> WHAT A REMARKABLE -- I MEAN,
OF ALL THE THINGS I DIDN'T THINK
I'D ACTUALLY DISCUSSING AS A
JOURNALIST, THIS IS JUST ONE
MORE TO PILE ON TO THE TOP.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
>>> UP NEXT, YOU HEAR IT A LOT
FROM THE 2020 DEMOCRATIC
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES.
THEY WANT TO INVEST IN
EDUCATION.
MOST OF THEM DON'T HAVE A VERY
DETAILED PLAN ON HOW THEY'D DO,
BUT SENATOR AMY KLOBUCHAR JUST
UNVEILED HERS.
I AM GOING TO TALK TO HER ABOUT
IT IN JUST A COUPLE MINUTES.
LATER THE PRESIDENT SAID HE
WOULD START A BIG DEPORTATION
PUSH AFTER THE FOURTH OF JULY.
I WILL TALK TO THE FORMER I.C.E.
CHIEF ABOUT WHAT GOES INTO
IMMIGRATION RAIDS NEXT.
YOU ARE WATCHING MSNBC.
XT
YOU ARE WATCHING MSNBC
When you book at Hilton.com, you
get the Price Match Guarantee.
So if you find your
room at a lower rate,
Hilton is like...
We're gonna match that rate
and give you an extra 25% off.
What would travel sites do if
you found a different price?
That's not my problem,
it's your problem.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
HAVE YOU BEEN TOLD YOU CAN'T GET
HIGH SPEED INTERNET WHERE YOU
LIVE? WELL YOU CAN, WITH
HUGHESNET GEN 5. EXPERIENCE THE
POWER OF NEXT GENERATION
SATELLITE INTERNET WHEREVER YOU
LIVE. HUGHESNET GEN 5 IS FAST.
YOU'LL GET 25MBPS, PLUS BUILT-IN
WI-FI, AND THERE'S NO HARD DATA
LIMITS. SO, WHEREVER YOU LIVE,
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
EVERYTHING YOU LOVE ONLINE.
CONNECT ON SOCIAL MEDIA, STAY
INFORMED, WATCH THE LATEST
VIDEOS, AND HELP YOUR KIDS GET
AHEAD. NO WONDER HUGHESNET IS
AMERICA'S NUMBER ONE CHOICE FOR
SATELLITE INTERNET. ACT NOW TO
SAVE BIG WITH OUR LIMITED TIME
OFFER. GET FREE STANDARD
INSTALLATION BY CALLING RIGHT
NOW. SO, WHAT ARE YOU WAITING
FOR? GET HUGHESNET GEN5. TO
ORDER, CALL THE NUMBER ON YOUR
SCREEN. BE SURE TO ASK ABOUT OUR
HOME PHONE SERVICE, TOO. CALL
THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN
TODAY.
>>> THE PARADES, PICNICS AND
OTHER FOURTH OF JULY EVENTS ARE
OVER AND THE PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES HAVE RETURNED TO
SERIOUS POLICY DISCUSSIONS.
TODAY A NUMBER OF THEM ARE
TALKING ABOUT EDUCATION.
TEN DEMOCRATIC CONTENDERS ARE
TAKING PART IN THE NATIONAL
EDUCATION ASSOCIATION'S STRONG
PUBLIC SCHOOLS PRESIDENTIAL
FORUM TAKING PLACE RIGHT NOW IN
HOUSTON.
BERNIE SANDERS, YOU CAN SEE, UP
THERE ON THE STAGE.
ONE OF THE CANDIDATES
PARTICIPATING IN TODAY'S EVENT
IS MINNESOTA SENATOR AMY
KLOBUCHAR WHOSE MOTHER WAS A
SECOND GRADE TEACHER.
A SHORT TIME AGO SHE UNVEILED A
NEW PROPOSAL CALLED PROGRESS
PARTNERSHIPS, A FEDERAL STATE
EFFORT TO PROVIDE ADDITIONAL
RESOURCES AND FUNDING FOR PUBLIC
SCHOOLS.
IN ORDER TO TAKE PART, STATES
WILL NEED TO DO OR HAVE ALREADY
DONE THE FOLLOWING THINGS.
WITH REGARD TO TEACHER PAY,
STATES WILL AGREE TO A STATE
FEDERAL PARTNERSHIP THAT
INCLUDES GENEROUS FEDERAL
MATCHES TO INCREASE SALARIES FOR
ALL TEACHERS.
STATES WILL ALSO HAVE TO WORK
WITH EDUCATORS TO DEVELOP AND
SUBMIT RECOMMENDATIONS ON HOW
SCHOOLS CAN MEET THE NEEDS OF
WORKING FAMILIES LIKE
AFTER-SCHOOL PROGRAMS,
ALTERNATIVE PROGRAMS, AND
COMMUNITY SCHOOLS.
THE PLAN ALSO CALLS FOR GENEROUS
FEDERAL FUNDING TO IMPROVE
SCHOOL INFRASTRUCTURE.
STATES WILL ALSO HAVE TO CREATE
A MECHANISM FOR DISTRIBUTING
THOSE FUNDS THAT MAKE SURE TO
ADDRESS DISPARITIES IN
CONDITIONS AND RESOURCES AND
PROVIDE EQUAL FUNDING FOR
DISTRICTS ACROSS THE STATE.
AND STATES WILL ALSO NEED TO
CONVENE A COMMISSION TO REVIEW
THEIR EXISTING EDUCATION FUNDING
FORMULA TO ENSURE THAT ALL
STUDENTS, PARTICULARLY THOSE
WITH THE GREATEST NEEDS, HAVE
ACCESS TO ADEQUATE EDUCATIONAL
RESOURCES.
SENATOR AMY KLOBUCHAR JOINS ME
NOW FROM THE NEA CONFERENCE IN
HOUSTON.
SHE IS A CONTENDER FOR THE
PRESIDENCY IN 020.
SENATOR, GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
>> WELL, THANKS, ALI.
THANKS FOR MENTIONING MY MOM.
SHE WOULD HAVE LOVED TO BE HERE
TODAY.
SHE TAUGHT SECOND GRADE UNTIL
SHE WAS 70 YEARS OLD.
>> WOW.
>> AND I STILL HAVE PEOPLE COME
UP TO ME AND SAY SHE WAS THEIR
FAVORITE TEACHER.
HER FAVORITE UNIT SHE TAUGHT WAS
THE MONARCH BUTTERFLY ONE WHERE
SHE WOULD DRESS UP WITH
ANTENNAS, TIGHTS, AND CARRY A
SIGN THAT SAID "TO MEXICO OR
BUST" BECAUSE THAT'S WHERE THE
MONARCH BUTTERFLIES FLEW.
THERE SHE IS.
SHE WAS A TEACHER OF THE YEAR
FOR HER DISTRICT A NUMBER OF
TIMES.
ONE OF THE THINGS THAT SHE HAD
THOUGHT VERY STRONGLY ABOUT WAS
THAT ALL KIDS, WHICH I HAVE NOW
INHERITED, ALL KIDS DESERVE A
RIGHT TO A GOOD EDUCATION.
AND THAT'S WHY I WENT TO PUBLIC
SCHOOL.
MY DAUGHTER WENT TO PUBLIC
SCHOOLS INCLUDING A NUMBER OF
YEARS IN A SCHOOL THAT WAS
NEARLY 90% FREE AND REDUCED
LUNCH.
SO I HAVE A SENSE OF WHAT'S
GOING ON THERE.
AND I CAN TELL YOU RIGHT NOW
THERE SHOULD BE MORE FEDERAL
INVESTMENT AND MORE FOCUS ON
EDUCATION.
IF WE WANT TO PARTICIPATE IN
THIS GLOBAL ECONOMY, OUR KIDS
HAVE TO BE ABLE TO DO A GOOD
JOB.
TO DO A GOOD JOB YOU NEED
TEACHERS.
AND TO RECRUIT GOOD TEACHERS,
YOU NEED TO HAVE GOOD PAY, AND
YOU NEED TO MAKE SURE THAT THE
KIDS ARE GETTING PREPARED FOR
THE JOBS WE HAVE AVAILABLE
TODAY.
>> SO WE HAVE 330 MILLION PEOPLE
IN THE UNITED STATES ROUGHLY.
WE HAVE 50 MILLION PUBLIC SCHOOL
STUDENTS IN 2017.
AND FUNDAMENTALLY THE
RESPONSIBILITY FOR EDUCATING
THOSE STUDENTS FALLS TO THE
STATES.
SO WHILE I AM DEEPLY
APPRECIATIVE OF THE THOUGHT THAT
GOES INTO PLANS LIKE YOURS AND
THE OTHER CANDIDATES, STATES IN
GENERAL HAVE BEEN UNDERFUNDING
VERY DELIBERATELY UNDERFUNDING
PUBLIC EDUCATION FOR DECADES
NOW.
WE HAVE CREATED A WORLD IN WHICH
PEOPLE LIKE YOUR MOTHER ARE NOT
TREATED THE WAY THEY SHOULD BE
IN TERMS OF THE RESPECT AND THE
PAY THEY SHOULD BE GIVEN.
NOW PUBLIC SCHOOLTEACHERS WHO
MAY EARN WHATEVER THEY EARN ARE
OFTEN TAKING MONEY OUT OF THEIR
OWN POCKETS TO BUY SUPPLIES FOR
THEIR OWN SCHOOLS.
HOW DO YOU SHIFT THAT
CONVERSATION.
>> MY MOM DID THAT.
SO THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT IS
SPENDING LIKE 3% OF EDUCATION
COSTS.
YOU SHOULD MOVE THAT UP.
LET ME TELL YOU EXACTLY WHAT YOU
SAID IS WHY I PUT THESE PROGRESS
PARTNERSHIPS FORWARD.
I THINK YOU NEED TO INCENTIVIZE
THE STATES TO DO MORE,
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT COMES TO
TEACHER PAY INFRASTRUCTURE,
THOSE THINGS.
YOU DO IT WITH GENEROUS MATCHING
GRANTS AND TO MAKE SURE THEY'RE
HEADED IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
THE SECOND THING, AND THIS IS A
PLAN A NUMBER OF US HAVE PUT
FORWARD, KAMALA HARRIS AND
OTHERS, ABOUT INCREASING TEACHER
PAY.
AND ONE OF THE WAYS YOU CAN DO
THIS IS BY PAYING FOR IT WITH
GOING BACK TO THE NUMBERS AND
THE ESTATE TAX THAT WE HAD
DURING THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
OR SOMEWHERE AROUND THAT.
AND THAT WOULD LITERALLY RAISE
ENOUGH MONEY TO SUBSTANTIALLY
INCREASE TEACHER PAY OR TALKING
HERE ABOUT THAT AS STATE TAX
EXEMPTION.
THAT WOULD BE SOMETHING THAT
WOULD BE REALLY HELPFUL TO
RECRUITING.
AND THAT'S FEDERAL MONEY.
THEN YOU ADD IDEAS LIKE MINE
WHICH IS TO INCENTIVIZE STATES
TO BE FOCUSING MORE ON TEACHERS
AND OUR SCHOOLS AND MAKING SURE
THAT WE HAVE MORE QUALITY IN OUR
SCHOOLS.
THAT'S THE WAY YOU DO IT.
>> SO WE HAVE TWO DIFFERENT
ISSUES THAT WE'RE DEALING WITH.
ONE IS TEACHER PAY.
I JUST WANT TO SHOW OUR VIEWERS
ACCORDING TO THE NATIONAL
EDUCATION ASSOCIATION HOSTING
THE EVENT YOU'RE AT, THE HIGHEST
TEACHER SALARIES ARE IN NEW
YORK, CALIFORNIA, AND
MASSACHUSETTS, UPWARD OF $80,000
A YEAR.
THE LOWEST IN MISSISSIPPI, WEST
VIRGINIA, AND OKLAHOMA IN THE
40s.
SO WE'VE GOT THAT PROBLEM THAT
YOU AND I DISCUSSED.
AND THEN WE'VE GOT THIS OTHER
ISSUE, AND THAT IS STATES WITH
THE HIGHEST AND LOWEST AVERAGE
SPENDING PER CAPITA ON STUDENT.
AGAIN, NEW YORK, WASHINGTON
STATE, AND NEW JERSEY SPEND
UPWARD OF $20,000 PER PUPIL.
IDAHO, UTAH, AND ARIZONA ARE
SPENDING 6, 7, AND $8,000 PER
PUPIL.
WE ARE NOWHERE CLOSE TO HAVING A
STANDARDIZED LEVEL OF EDUCATION
IF YOU LOOK AT IT THROUGH
FUNDING IN THIS COUNTRY.
>> RIGHT.
THAT IS WHY UPPING THE FEDERAL
ROLE, PUTTING IN AN EDUCATION
SECRETARY WHO IS NOT BETSY
DeVOS, MAKING SURE THAT WE HAVE
POLICYMAKERS IN PLACE THAT
UNDERSTAND WHAT EDUCATION MEANS
AND HOW IMPORTANT IT IS FOR
INDIVIDUAL FAMILIES BUT ALSO FOR
THE FUTURE OF OUR COUNTRY WHEN
WE'RE TRYING TO COMPETE IN A
GLOBAL ECONOMY.
AND THEN I THINK ONE REALLY
INTERESTING ISSUE WAS
APPRENTICESHIPS AND DOING MORE
WITH COMMUNITY COLLEGES AT THE
HIGH SCHOOL LEVEL.
SO THAT'S A LOT ABOUT WHAT WE
ARE GOING TO BE TALKING ABOUT
TODAY.
I CAN TELL YOU SCHOOL, COLLEGE,
THOSE ARE THINGS THAT PEOPLE
BROUGHT INTO THE PARADES.
I'VE BECOME THE ONLY CANDIDATE
THAT WENT THE LAST THREE DAYS
HAVE BEEN IN IOWA, NEW
HAMPSHIRE, AND HOUSTON.
PEOPLE BRING UP SCHOOL A LOT.
THAT IS CORE TO THEIR FAMILIES.
AS SOMEONE THAT DIDN'T COME FROM
MONEY THAT STANDS HERE TODAY AS
A CANDIDATE FOR PRESIDENT AFTER
BEING THE GRANDDAUGHTER OF AN
IRON ORE MINER WHO COULDN'T
FINISH HIGH SCHOOL AND THE
DAUGHTER OF A TEACHER AND A
NEWSPAPER MAN, I CAN WALK THE
WALK WHEN IT COMES TO THE
IMPORTANCE OF EDUCATION.
AND THAT'S WHAT I AM GOING TO BE
TALKING ABOUT TODAY ON THAT
STAGE.
>> SENATOR, ONE OF THE OTHER
TOPICS THAT WE COVER VERY
CLOSELY ON THIS SHOW IS THE
ISSUE OF DATA PRIVACY AND
MANAGEMENT WITH FACEBOOK.
ROGER McNAMEE TALKS VERY FONDLY
OF THE FACT THAT YOU -- YOU
DON'T GET A LOT OF PRESS FOR
THIS, BUT YOU PUT A LOT OF
THINKING INTO HOW TO DEAL WITH
SILICON VALLEY AND TECH.
GIVE US A BIT OF YOUR IDEA ABOUT
HOW YOU DEAL WITH THE VERY
PRESSING AND ALMOST DAILY
CONCERNS THAT WE ARE HEARING
ABOUT HOW THESE COMPANIES
OPERATE AND MANAGE OUR
INFORMATION.
>> I THINK THEY THOUGHT THEY
COULD JUST RUN THE TABLES AND NO
ONE WOULD CARE BECAUSE THEY'RE
SUCCESSFUL COMPANIES.
I DON'T LIKE TO TAKE SUCCESS
AWAY FROM THEM, THAT'S GREAT.
BUT THE POINT IS WE NEED A
COUNTERBALANCE HERE.
AND THE FIRST THING WE NEED IS
PRIVACY RULES IN PLACE.
AND THEY'VE BEEN ABLE TO SAY,
NO, WE ARE JUST A FORUM.
NO THEY'RE NOT.
THEY ARE MEDIA COMPANIES.
THEY HAVE MADE TONS OF MONEY OFF
INDIVIDUALS.
ONE OF THE FEW BIPARTISAN BILLS
OUT THERE TO DO IT WITH MAKING
SURE THAT THERE ARE RULES IN
PLACE SO PEOPLE CAN PROTECT
THEIR PRIVATE DATA IS FIRST.
YOU ALSO HAVE TO MAKE SURE THAT
WHEN THEY'RE SHARING DATA THAT
THERE'S RULES ABOUT THAT.
AND I WOULD SUGGEST THAT THEY
HAVE TO PAY A FEE, A TAX, SO
THAT MONEY CAN GO BACK INTO OUR
NATION'S CYBERSECURITY TO
PROTECT US.
AND THE THIRD THING IS ALL ABOUT
DEMOCRACY.
IF WE DON'T DO SOMETHING ABOUT
THIS BEFORE THE NEXT ELECTION,
WHEN WE HAVE A PRESIDENT SENDING
OUT DOCTORED VIDEOS OF SPEAKER
PELOSI, SHE'S STRONG, SHE IS
GOING TO BE ABLE TO PROTECT
HERSELF.
BUT IF THIS IS WHAT OUR
CAMPAIGNS ARE GOING TO COME TO,
VIDEOS WHERE YOU CAN'T EVEN TELL
IF IT'S THE PERSON OR NOT, WE
HAVE A MAJOR PROBLEM.
SO MAKING THOSE COMPANIES PUT
SOME RULES OF THE ROAD IN PLACE
WHEN IT COMES TO WHO'S BUYING
ADS, WHO IS PAYING FOR THOSE
ADS, WHAT THOSE ADS ARE SO OTHER
CAMPAIGNS AND THE MEDIA CAN SEE
THEM IS GOING TO BE CRITICAL.
WHY SHOULD YOUR NETWORK HAVE TO
FOLLOW THOSE RULES, AND THEN
THESE OTHER BILLION DOLLAR
COMPANIES DON'T?
IT MAKES NO SENSE AT ALL.
AND AS WE KNOW FROM 2016, IT
PAYS A MAJOR ROLE IN SPREADING
FAKE NEWS AND ALSO ALLOWING
BASICALLY FOR FOREIGN COUNTRIES
TO HAVE INFLUENCE ON OUR
ELECTION.
AND WHEN I HEARD THE PRESIDENT
MAKE A JOKE ABOUT MEDDLING WHEN
HE WAS AT THE G20, THAT'S JUST
WHAT WE ARE DEALING WITH RIGHT
NOW.
WE ARE IN JULY 4th WEEK, WE KNOW
THAT MILLIONS OF PEOPLE
SACRIFICED SERVING OUR COUNTRY
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF THEM
DYING, SERVING OUR COUNTRY.
THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENED.
AND YET HE MAKES A JOKE ABOUT
IT.
IT'S NOT A JOKE NOT TO THOSE WHO
HAVE SERVED TO PROTECT OUR
FREEDOM.
>> I WANT TO ASK YOU ONE LAST
QUESTION.
YOU ARE FROM MINNESOTA AND YOU
ARE ON THE AGRICULTURE
COMMITTEE.
JUST IN THE LAST HOUR I SPEAK TO
A CONSERVATIVE ECONOMIST WHO
SAID THAT WHILE FARMERS ARE
SUFFERING BECAUSE OF THE TRADE
WAR, THE AMOUNT OF SUBSIDY THEY
GET FROM THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT
ALLOWS THEM TO JUSTIFY
CONTINUING TO SUPPORT THE
PRESIDENT IN THESE TRADE WARS.
WHAT'S YOUR TAKE ON THAT?
>> MY TAKE IS THAT THE FARMERS I
KNOW, THEY JUST WANT TO MAKE A
LIVING.
THEY KNOW VERY WELL IS THE MORE
THEIR SOY BEANS SIT AT THEIR
FARMS OR THEY ARE UNABLE TO SELL
GOODS TO MARKET, THE MORE THOSE
CONTRACTS ARE GOING TO FARMERS
IN OTHER COUNTRIES AND FOREIGN
LANDS.
IT'S GOING TO BE HARDER AND
HARDER.
THEY CAN'T JUST GET THOSE
CONTRACTS BACK IN A MONTH.
SO THEY'RE LONG-TERM VIABILITY.
WE HAVE HAD MORE AND MORE FARM
BANKRUPTCIES, ESPECIALLY FOR THE
SMALL FARMERS.
SO MY FOCUS AS A SENIOR MEMBER
OF THE AGRICULTURE COMMITTEE AND
MY FOCUS AS PRESIDENT WILL BE TO
MAKE SURE THAT WE KEEP OUR FOOD
SUPPLY IN AMERICA.
WE DO THAT WITH A SPECIAL FOCUS
ON OUR SMALL FARMERS.
I HAVE A VERY STRONG TRACK
RECORD OF MAKING SURE THESE
PAYMENTS AREN'T GOING TO THE
BEVERLY HILLS 90210 AREA CODE
THAT THEY ARE GOING INSTEAD TO
OUR SMALL FARMERS.
AND THEN MAKING SURE THAT IF
WE'RE GOING TO PUSH ON TRADE
WHICH WE SHOULD DO THAT WE'RE
NOT USING A MEAT CLEAVER LIKE
THIS PRESIDENT HAS DONE OR WE
CAN CALL IT A TWEET CLEAVER.
BUT INSTEAD THAT WE ARE FOCUSED
ON TARGETED TARIFFS AND TARGETED
TRADE POLICIES THAT ARE REALLY
GOING TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
THAT'S WHAT I'M CONCERNED ABOUT
THAT'S GOING ON IN THE MIDWEST.
I AM SOMEONE THAT'S WON IN THOSE
RED DISTRICTS.
I HAVE WON IN 42 OF THE COUNTIES
THAT TRUMP WON IN MY STATE.
I THINK THE FARMERS WANT TO MAKE
A DECENT LIVING AND THEY WANT
SOMEONE WHO CAN LOOK THEM IN THE
EYE AND TELL THEM THE TRUTH.
THEY DON'T ALWAYS AGREE WITH,
BUT TELL THEM THE TRUTH.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT THIS
PRESIDENT REALLY DOES.
>> SENATOR AMY KLOBUCHAR, THANK
YOU FOR TAKING TIME TO TALK TO
US TODAY.
>> IT WAS GREAT TO BE ON.
>> AMY KLOBUCHAR, CANDIDATE FOR
PRESIDENT, AND SHE IS A SENATOR
FROM MINNESOTA.
>>> STILL AHEAD, THE PRESIDENT
PROMISED TO CRACK DOWN ON
ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION AFTER THE
FOURTH OF JULY.
THE HOLIDAY HAS COME AND GONE,
AND PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS THE
RAIDS WILL START SOON.
WILL STAR.
(Gasp)
(Singsong)
Budget meeting!
Sweet.
If you compare last quarter
to this quarter...
Various: Mmm.
It's no wonder everything
seems a little better
with the creamy taste
of Philly,
made with fresh milk
and real cream.
with the creamy taste
of Philly,
“Shaving has been difficult for
me
I have very sensitive skin,
and I get ingrowing hairs”
“Just stopping that
irritation....
That burn that I get.
I wouldn't use anything else”
♪
Going to the Shawn Mendes
Verizon UP concert
was like an
out of body experience.
We were right in front of him.
Dead center. Front row.
'Cause actually, Zarmina,
you touched Shawn Mendes.
Yeah, I touched him!
She touched Shawn Mendes!
He like held my hand
for a while.
And then we got
to meet him after,
which was like...
Another surprise.
Yeah.
We love Verizon even more now.
I'll never forget
that day. Ever.
(VO)
The network more people rely on,
gives you more.
Like thousands of tickets
to concerts,
festivals and private shows.
And big savings on
our best phones when you switch.
That's Verizon.
Too many people in
pain settle
for a restless night's sleep.
There's a better
choice. Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid
and the 12-hour pain-relieving
strength of Aleve
that dares to
last into the morning.
So you feel refreshed.
ALEVE PM.
There's a better choice.
(birds chirping)
(KICKSTART MY HEART
BY MOTLEY CRUE)
(truck honks)
(wheels screeching)
(clapping)
(sound of can hitting
bag and bowl)
I'M ALEX TREBEK,
HERE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
(clapping)
Always there in crunch time.
IF YOU'RE AGE 50 TO 85,
AND LOOKING TO BUY LIFE
INSURANCE ON A FIXED BUDGET,
REMEMBER THE THREE P'S.
-THE THREE P'S?
-WHAT ARE THE THREE P'S?
THE THREE P'S OF LIFE INSURANCE
ON A FIXED BUDGET
ARE PRICE, PRICE,
AND PRICE.
A PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD,
A PRICE THAT CAN'T INCREASE,
AND A PRICE
THAT FITS YOUR BUDGET.
I'M 65 AND TAKE MEDICATIONS.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
YOU CAN GET COVERAGE
FOR $9.95 A MONTH.
I JUST TURNED 80.
WHAT'S MY PRICE?
$9.95 A MONTH
FOR YOU TOO.
CALL NOW ABOUT
THE #1 MOST POPULAR
WHOLE LIFE INSURANCE PLAN,
AVAILABLE THROUGH
THE COLONIAL PENN PROGRAM.
NO MEDICAL EXAM,
NO HEALTH QUESTIONS.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE
IS GUARANTEED.
SO CALL NOW
FOR FREE INFORMATION.
>>> I DON'T CALL THEM RAIDS, I
SAY THEY CAME IN ILLEGALLY AND
WE BRING THEM OUT LEGALLY.
THEY WILL BE STARTING FAIRLY
SOON, BUT I DON'T CALL THEM
RAIDS.
>> THAT WAS PRESIDENT TRUMP
EARLIER TALKING ABOUT THE I.C.E.
RAIDS THAT HE'S BEEN PROMISING.
THE PRESIDENT INITIALLY DELAYED
THE RAIDS ON JUNE 22nd, A DAY
BEFORE THEY WERE SET TO BEGIN
SAYING HE'D GIVE CONGRESS TWO
WEEKS TO WORK ON ASYLUM LAWS AND
HALT THE FLOW OF U.S. MIGRANTS.
BUT SINCE THEN NO COMPREHENSIVE
IMMIGRATION REFORM DEAL HAS BEEN
REACHED.
WITH ME NOW JOHN, GOOD TO SEE
YOU AGAIN.
THIS IS TRICKY, WHETHER THE
PRESIDENT WANTS TO CALL THEM
RAIDS OR NOT, THEY ARE SOME SORT
OF ENFORCEMENT ACTION THAT
REQUIRES SOME DEGREE OF
PLANNING.
AND THERE WERE SOME PEOPLE YOU
AND I TALKED ABOUT THIS LAST
TIME.
THERE WERE SOME PEOPLE WHO SAID
THE PRESIDENT BY CONTINUING TO
ANNOUNCE THESE THINGS AND TALK
ABOUT THEM IN THE MEDIA ACTUALLY
COMPROMISES THE WORK THAT HE
MIGHT BE TRYING TO ACHIEVE.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
LISTEN, HAVING BEEN INVOLVED IN
A NUMBER OF THESE OPERATIONS AND
WHETHER YOU CALL THEM RAIDS OR
WHATEVER YOU CALL THEM, THESE
ENFORCEMENT ACTIONS.
THE NUMBER ONE RULE IS YOU DON'T
TIP THE TARGET IN ADVANCE
BECAUSE THEN WHEN YOU GO TO THE
HOUSE OF THE LOCATION WHERE YOU
THINK THAT TARGET IS, THEY ARE
SIMPLY NOT THERE.
AT THE BEGINNING OF THE
OPERATION WE'D GET SOMETHING
LIKE 90% OF THE PEOPLE WE WERE
GOING AFTER.
BUT AFTER TIME THAT WAS
DISSIPATE AND PEOPLE FLED AND
HID.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS SAID THAT
PUBLIC SAFETY IS THE REASON FOR
THESE RAIDS BUT NEW DOCUMENTS
ACTUALLY SHOW THAT I.C.E. IS
BUILDING TARGET LISTS FOR THESE
MASS ROUNDUPS OF PEOPLE BASED ON
TARGET NUMBERS THAT THEY HAVE TO
MEET.
SO THE QUESTION IS DO THESE
PUBLIC DOCUMENTS, YOU KNOW,
THESE THINGS SORT OF HURT THE
ARGUMENT THAT THERE'S A PUBLIC
SAFETY NEED FOR THESE RAIDS?
>> ALI, IT'S NOT GOING TO BE
PUBLIC SAFETY.
THE PROBLEM HERE IS THIS.
THE PRESIDENT WANTS BIG NUMBERS.
BUT TO GET BIG NUMBERS WHAT,
THAT REQUIRES TYPICALLY IS YOU
GO AFTER THE MOST VULNERABLE
POPULATION.
THE CRIMINAL ALE YETION
POPULATION IS ACTUALLY THE MOST
DIFFICULT TO FIND.
THEY'RE ADEPT AT HIDING AND
USING ALIASES.
IT TAKES MUCH MORE LEG WORK THAN
IT DOES A FAMILY WITH CHILDREN
WHO ARE SITTING IN A STATIC
LOCATION.
SO I DON'T THINK THIS OPERATION
AT ALL IS GOING TO PROMOTE
PUBLIC SAFETY.
YOU COULD ARGUE THAT IT HELPS
PROMOTE THE INTEGRITY OF OUR
IMMIGRATION COURT SYSTEM OR THE
BORDER SECURITY BUT CERTAINLY
NOT PUBLIC SAFETY.
>> THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IS
THREATENING TO IMPOSE HUGE FINES
ON PEOPLE WHO DISOBEY
DEPORTATION ORDERS.
SOME OF THEM UPWARDS OF
$300,000.
TALK TO ME ABOUT THAT.
>> WELL, I MEAN, THERE ARE
CERTAIN SITUATIONS IN THE LAW IN
WHICH YOU CAN IMPOSE A FINE ON
AN INDIVIDUAL.
I CAN TELL YOU COLLECTING IT IS
A DIFFERENT STORY ENTIRELY.
I AM NOT SURE HOW THEY INTEND TO
COLLECT THEM AGAINST A MAJORITY
OF THESE INDIVIDUALS.
IF SOME INDIVIDUAL IS LATER ABLE
TO LEGALLY ENTER THE UNITED
STATES, BUT THE REALITY IS THE
VAST, VAST MAJORITY OF PEOPLE
WHO ARE DEPORTED FROM THIS
COUNTRY ARE NEVER ABLE TO
LEGALLY RETURN TO THE UNITED
STATES.
>> THERE IS WIDE AGREEMENT ON
CERTAIN IMMIGRATION ISSUES IN
THIS COUNTRY.
FOR INSTANCE, ON THE DREAMERS,
THE DACA KIDS, THE OVERWHELMING
SUPPORT FOR HAVING THEM STAY
HERE BECAUSE THEY HAVE TO FOLLOW
RULES.
THEY'VE GROWN UP HERE, THEY ARE
EITHER GETTING AN EDUCATION OR
WORKING, THEY CAN'T COMMIT
SERIOUS CRIMES.
BUT THERE ARE OTHER
DISAGREEMENTS ABOUT OTHER BASIC
THINGS AND SOME DEMOCRATIC
CANDIDATES HAVE ACTUALLY TALKED
ABOUT DECRIMINALIZING THE ACT OF
ILLEGALLY ENTERING THE UNITED
STATES.
JOE BIDEN JOE BIDEN SAID TODAY
THAT ILLEGAL BORDER CROSSINGS
SHOULD NOT BE DECRIMINALIZED.
THIS IS A VERY INTERESTING PLACE
THAT DEMOCRATS ARE IN.
BECAUSE A LOT OF AMERICANS WHO
ARE SYMPATHETIC TO IMMIGRANTS
AND ASYLUM-SEEKERS MAY NOT
BELIEVE THAT DECRIMINALIZING THE
ACT OF COMING INTO THE UNITED
STATES ILLEGALLY SHOULD BE PART
OF THE EQUATION.
>> YEAH.
I AGREE WITH THE VICE PRESIDENT
ON THIS ONE.
LISTEN, IF YOU COME ACROSS THE
BORDER WITHOUT INSPECTING, THAT
IS A CRIME, IT'S A MISDEMEANOR
OFFENSE FOR YOUR FIRST OFFENSE.
SO IT'S NOT THAT SERIOUS OF
CRIME, BUT IT SHOULD REMAIN A
CRIME.
LOOK, THERE IS A ROLE FOR BORDER
SECURITY, BORDER ENFORCEMENT.
THERE IS A ROLE FOR.
I THINK A LOT OF ISSUE WITH THE
MANNER IN WHICH THIS
ADMINISTRATION IS DEALING WITH
THAT IS A DETRIMENT TO PUBLIC
SAFETY.
THEY ARE FOCUSED ON VULNERABLE.
BECAUSE OF THE PRESIDENT'S
POLICIES THAT WE ARE NOW LOOKING
AT IMMIGRATION ENFORCEMENT IN
LARGE RATHER THAN QUESTIONING
THE SPECIFIC TACTICS THIS
ADMINISTRATION IS DOING WHEN
THERE IS AN IMPORTANT ROLE FOR
ALL OF OUR PUBLIC SAFETY IN THE
FUNCTIONS THAT I.C.E. AND CVP DO
EVERY IDEA.
>> BUT WHAT THE DOES -- IS WHAT
THE PRESIDENT IS DOING, IS THAT
PLAYING INTO THE HANDS OF THE
PRESIDENT HIMSELF BECAUSE HE
PROVOKES A REACTION THAT CAUSES
SOME DEMOCRATS TO SAY LET'S
DECRIMINALIZE THE OPERATION AND
THEN THE PRESIDENT CAN GO OUT
AND SAY THAT SOUNDS LIKE OPEN
BORDERS WHICH HE'S BEEN ACCUSING
DEMOCRATS OF EMBRACING THE WHOLE
TIME?
>> I THINK THAT'S RIGHT, ALI.
I THINK THAT, YOU KNOW, LOOK.
A LOT OF THE PRESIDENT'S CHATTER
REALLY IS IDLE THREATS.
HE'S TALKED ABOUT A MILLION
PEOPLE APPREHENDED.
I.C.E. HAS NO CAPACITY TO ARREST
A MILLION PEOPLE.
AN OPERATION LIKE THIS IN A
TWO-WEEK PERIOD IS GOING TO GET
5,000 AND THAT'S PROBABLY OPT
MIST.
BUT IT DOES TRIGGER THIS
REACTION OF THIS ABOLISH I.C.E.
I THINK THE MAJORITY OF THE
PUBLIC RECOGNIZES THAT I.C.E.
PLAYS A CRITICAL ROLE IN OUR
PUBLIC SAFETY.
I DO THINK A LOT OF PEOPLE, NOT
ENOUGH RECOGNIZE TOO THAT ISIS
IS A CRITICAL PLAYER IN THE
COUNTERTERRORISM EFFORT.
THEY SAVE MORE CHILDREN FROM
EXPLOITATION THAN ANY OTHER
FEDERAL AGENCY, STOPPING NORTH
KOREA AND IRAN FROM GETTING
SENSITIVE TECHNOLOGIES.
BUT IT PLAYS INTO THE HANDS WHEN
YOU START TALKING ABOUT THESE
EXTREMIST POSITIONS THAT WE NEED
TO GET RID OF THE BORDER PATROL
OR I.C.E. SIMPLY BECAUSE OF THE
ADMINISTRATION'S POLICIES, NOT
NECESSARILY BECAUSE OF THE
AGENCIES THEMSELVES.
>> JOHN IS A FORMER ACTING
DIRECTOR OF I.C.E.
>>> COMING UP NEXT WE ARE GOING
TO TAKE A LOOK AT AMERICA'S
ENERGY REVOLUTION.
FOR THE FIRST TIME THE UNITED
STATES IS PRODUCING MORE ENERGY
FROM RENEWABLES THAN IT IS
FROMCOAL.
I'M GOING TO TALK TO AN AUTHOR
WHO BUILT ONE OF THE BIGGEST
WIND EMPIRES IN THE COUNTRY.
YOU ARE WATCHING MSNBC.
TRY.
YOU ARE WATCHING MSNBC
[ Alarm beeping ]
Wake up!
There's a lot
that needs to get done today.
Small things. Big things.
Too hard to do alone things.
Day after day,
you need to get it all done.
And here to listen
and help you through it all
is Bank of America.
With the expertise and know-how
you need
to reach that blissful state
of Done-ness.
So let's get after it.
♪ Everything is all right ♪
What would you like
the power to do?®
♪ All right ♪
At Hilton.com,
What would you like
the power to do?®
I can choose from all their
different hotel brands...
Like a DoubleTree
for my cousins.
A Homewood Suites
for my uncle.
A Hampton for
my sister and her kids.
And the Waldorf Astoria
Beverly Hills for me.
Can I get a..?
Thank you.
Book at Hilton.com
and get the Hilton
Price Match Guarantee.
♪ When you have nausea,
heartburn, ♪
♪ indigestion, upset stomach,
diarrhea ♪
Try New Pepto Liquicaps for fast
relief and ultra-coating.
♪ Nausea, heartburn,
indigestion, upset stomach,
diarrhea ♪
Get powerful relief with new
Pepto Bismol Liquicaps.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
WE ARE TAKING A CLOSER LOOK INTO
A BIG ECONOMIC OPPORTUNITY IN
THE FIGHT AGAINST CLIMATE
CHANGE.
CLEAN ENERGY.
HERE'S SOMETHING YOU MAY HAVE
MISSED.
FOR THE FIRST TIME OUR CAPACITY
FOR CREATING ELECTRICITY FROM
RENEWABLE ENERGY SOURCES
SURPASSED THAT FOR COAL.
AS THE L.A. TIMES POINTS OUT,
DOMESTIC COAL PRODUCTION AND USE
HAVE DROPPED TO THEIR LOWEST
LEVELS IN FOUR DECADES EVEN
THOUGH THE ECONOMY IS MORE THAN
TWICE THE SIZE IT WAS 40 YEARS
AGO.
ADDITIONALLY, MORE COAL-FIRED
POWER PLANTS HAVE SHUT DOWN SO
FAR DURING THE TRUMP PRESIDENCY
THAN THROUGH ALL EIGHT YEARS OF
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION.
AND IT MAY HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE COST.
LET ME SHOW YOU A MAP OF THE
LEAST EXPENSIVE TECHNOLOGIES FOR
GENERATING ELECTRICITY ACROSS
THE UNITED STATES BY COUNTY.
HERE YOU CAN SEE HOW -- LET ME
JUST SHOW YOU THE COLORS HERE.
THE BLUE IS WIND.
GREEN IS NATURAL GAS.
THE YELLOW -- THE GOLD IS SOLAR,
THE YELLOW IS ALSO SOLAR.
ONE OF THEM IS FOR UTILITIES
THAT GENERATE ELECTRICITY.
THE LIGHTER YELLOW IS FOR
RESIDENTIAL USE AND THE GRAY OF
COURSE IS COAL.
COAL REPRESENTS THE SMALLEST
PROPORTION.
JOINING ME NOW IS RUSSELL GOLD.
HE IS A SENIOR ENERGY REPORTER
FOR THE WALL STREET JOURNAL" AND
OFFER OF A NEW BOOK, SUPERPOWER.
ONE MAN'S QUEST TO TRANSFORM
ENERGY.
IT PROFILES MICHAEL SKELLY WHO
BEGAN DEVELOPING WIND ENERGY
INFRASTRUCTURE AND WENT ON TO
BUILD THE SECOND LARGEST WIND
POWER COMPANY IN THE UNITED
STATES.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> I WANT TO JUST READ FROM YOUR
BOOK.
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT MICHAEL
SKELLY.
AND YOU SAID HE WAS A DEPARTURE
FROM WIND FARM BUILDER WHO WERE
MORE INTERESTED IN CREATING
SUSTAINABLE ENERGY THAN
SUSTAINABLE BUSINESSES.
SKELLY WANTED TO MAKE A PROFIT
BECAUSE PROFITS WOULD ATTRACT
NEW INVESTORS AND MONEY INTO
RENEWABLE ENERGY THIS HAS LONG
BEEN THE HOLY GRAIL.
IF YOU CAN MAKE SUSTAINABLE AND
RENEWABLE, PROFITABLE, IT CAN
REPLACE SORT OF OLDER-FASHIONED
DIRTIER ENERGY.
>> AND WE ARE SEEING THAT HAPPEN
RIGHT NOW.
WITH THE MAP YOU JUST BROUGHT UP
THERE IS A BIG PART OF THE
MIDDLE OF THE COUNTRY WHERE YOU
CAN GENERATE WIND AT A REALLY
LOW COST.
THE QUESTION RIGHT NOW IS HOW
FAST CAN THAT TRANSITION HAPPEN?
HOW FAST CAN YOU BRING IN MORE
RENEWABLES AT THIS LOWER PRICE?
>> AND WHAT ARE THE HEADWINDS
AND WHAT ARE THE TAILWINDS FOR
PEOPLE WHO ARE TRYING TO BRING
RENEWABLE ENERGY TO MARKET
FASTER?
>> WELL, TAILWINDS RIGHT NOW AS
WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT ARE
COST.
RENEWABLE ENERGY, WIND, AND
INCREASINGLY SOLAR, IS THE
LOW-COST WAY TO GENERATE
ELECTRICITY.
IT BEATS COAL, INCREASINGLY IT
BEATS NATURAL GAS, AND IT BEATS
NUCLEAR.
THE HEADWINDS ARE RIGHT NOW
WHERE YOU CAN GENERATE RENEWABLE
ENERGY INEXPENSIVELY IS THE
MIDDLE OF THE COUNTRY.
AND THAT'S NOT EXACTLY WHERE THE
FACTORIES ARE, THE PEOPLE ARE.
SO THE QUESTION IS HOW DO YOU
GET THAT ELECTRICITY FROM THE
MIDDLE OF THE COUNTRY TO THE
COASTS?
AND THAT'S ONE OF THE CHALLENGES
THAT MICHAEL SKELLY TACKLED AND
I WROTE ABOUT IN MY NEW BOOK
"SUPERPOWER."
I WOULD SAY ONE OF THE MAJOR
HEADWINDS ARE ELECTRIC UTILITIES
AND GENERATORS WHO DON'T WANT
THIS CHANGED BECAUSE QUITE
FRANKLY THEY ARE VERY GOOD AT
GENERATING ELECTRICITY FROM COAL
AND FROM SOME OF THE OLDER
RESOURCES, AND THEY DON'T WANT
TO MAKE THIS CHANGE BECAUSE THAT
WOULD MEAN LESS OPPORTUNITY FOR
THEM.
>> MOST PEOPLE SWITCH ON A LIGHT
AND HOPE THAT IT GOES ON.
THEY DON'T THINK MUCH ABOUT THE
BACKBONE AND THE INFRASTRUCTURE
OF WHERE THEIR POWER COMES FROM.
WHAT IS REQUIRED?
WHAT ARE THE INFRASTRUCTURE
REQUIREMENTS TO MAKE A WHOLESALE
SHIFT INTO RENEWABLES?
>> WELL, FIRST OF ALL THAT'S A
GREAT QUESTION.
FIRST OF ALL I'M NOT TALKING
ABOUT 100% RENEWABLE
ELECTRICITY.
>> RIGHT.
>> BECAUSE ONCE YOU GET ABOVE
08% IT GETS REALLY EXPENSIVE.
BUT WE CAN GET UP TO 70, 80% OF
OUR ELECTRICITY COMING FROM
RENEWABLE RESOURCES AT THE SAME
PRICES OR PERHAPS EVEN LOWER
THAN WE ARE RIGHT NOW WHAT'S
REQUIRED THE BIG PIECE OF
INFRASTRUCTURE THAT'S REQUIRED
IS TRANSMISSION.
THESE ARE BIG ELECTRICITY LINES
THAT CAN MOVE GIGAWATTS OF
ELECTRICITY AROUND.
THINK ABOUT IT LIKE YOUR
INTERSTATE HIGHWAYS.
WE HAVE TWO-LANE ROADS GOING ALL
OVER THE PLACE.
IN THE 1950s WE SAID LET'S BUILD
THESE HIGHWAYS SO WE CAN MOVE
PEOPLE QUICKLY AND EFFICIENTLY
FROM ONE CITY TO ANOTHER.
THAT'S REALLY WHAT WE NEED TO DO
RIGHT NOW WITH OUR TRANSMISSION.
>> I APPRECIATE THE BOOK AND I
APPRECIATE YOU COMING TO TALK
ABOUT IT.
HE IS THE AUTHOR OF THE NEW BOOK
"SUPERPOWER."
STILL AHEAD A JUDGE GAVE
LENIENCY TO A TEENAGE RAPE
SUSPECT BECAUSE THE JUDGE SAID
THE TEEN CAME FROM A GOOD
FAMILY.
I AM GOING TO TALK ABOUT HOW
THIS CASE FITS INTO A BROADER
CASE.
>>> HE CAME FROM A GOOD FAMILY,
A JUDGE USED THAT EXCUSE TO SHOW
LENIENCY TO A SUSPECT ACCUSED OF
SEXUAL ASSAULT AND IT'S
PROMPTING RENEWED DEBATE ABOUT
RAPE CULTURE IN THE UNITED
STATES.
THE CASE CAME FROM NEW JERSEY
WHERE A JUDGE DENIED THE REQUEST
TO TREAT THE 16-YEAR-OLD AS AN
ADULT, WHERE THE ASSAULT WAS
RECORDED AND SENT TO A VIDEO
TEXT SAYING, WHEN THE FIRST TIME
WITH SEX WAS RAPE.
HE COULD BE ACCUSED IN JUVENILE
COURT CASE AS 15 YEARS OR OLDER
BUT THE FAMILY COURT JUDGE
DENIED THE PROSECUTOR'S MOTION
SAYING THE THE SALT WASN'T RAPE
SAYING THIS YOUNG MAN CAME FROM
A GOOD FAMILY WHERE HE WAS DOING
VERY WELL.
AND HE WAS A CANDIDATE NOT JUST
FOR COLLEGE BUT A VERY GOOD
COLLEGE.
HIS SCORES FOR COLLEGE ENTRY
WERE VERY HIGH.
STATE APPEALS COURT ALREADY
OVERTURNED THE JUDGE'S DECISION
BUT THE CASE UNDERSCORES A
FUNDAMENTAL ISSUE IN THE WAY
THIS COUNTRY VIEWS RAPE AND
SEXUAL ASSAULT.
TO TALK TO THOSE ISSUE I TALK TO
MISS BURKE, THE FOUNDER OF THE
ME TOO MOVEMENT.
YOU HAVE REALLY APPROACHED THIS
FROM A DEGREE OF DIFFICULTY THAT
WE ARE LOOKING AT A LOW BASE
FROM UNDERSTANDING OF THESE
THINGS AND WHAT IS THE BEST WAY
TO GET US TO UNDERSTAND WHAT THE
SEXUAL VIOLENCE IS ALL ABOUT.
>> THIS IS WHY THE CONVERSATION
HAS TO SHIFT BETWEEN WHAT ME TOO
IS.
THIS WHOLE GLARING CASE IS
THERE'S NO CONVERSATION ABOUT
THE SURVIVAL, HER GRADES, HOW
HER LIFE CHANGED AND IT'S
FOCUSED TOTALLY ON THIS
PERPETRATOR.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS A LOT.
WHEN I REALIZE MORE SO IN THE
PAST FEW YEARS IS PEOPLE DON'T
UNDERSTAND THE LIFE CYCLE OF A
SURVIVOR.
THEY DON'T WHAT SEXUAL VIOLENCE
IS OR IT DOES TO THE PEOPLE THAT
EXPERIENCE IT.
SO YOU HAVE CASES LIKE THIS
HAPPEN WHERE YOU HAVE LARGER
NARRATIVES THAT ARE PATRIARCHAL
AND MISOGYNISTIC AND WHAT BOYS
AND GIRLS NEED MORE SO THAN WHO
THEY VICTIMIZE.
>> AND THE SAME ON COLLEGE
CAMPUSES WHEN WE TALK ABOUT BOYS
HAVING THEIR FUTURES RUINED
BECAUSE OF THE WAY THEIR
ASSAULTS WERE BEING TREATED.
WHAT DOES THE ASSAULT LOOK FOR
YOU LIKE ON THIS FRONT?
I DON'T THIB ANYBODY THAT'S A
PERPETRATOR NEEDS ALL OF THE
BOOK THROWN AT THEM BUT WE'RE
NOT LISTENING TO THE OTHER SIDE,
WE'RE NOT BALANCING OUT VICTIMS'
RIGHTS WITH PERPETRATORS'
RIGHTS.
>> THIS IS IT WHEN ME TOO CAME
TOGETHER, WE HAD PEOPLE SAYING
MY LIFE HAD BEEN AFFECTED BY
THIS THING.
WE HAVE YET TO TALK ABOUT THAT
THING AND WHAT SEXUAL VIOLENCE
IS AND HOW IT IMPACTS PEOPLE IN
THIS COUNTRY.
WHAT IT WILL TAKE IS A SHIFT IN
THE NARRATIVE ABOUT HOW WE TALK
ABOUT SEXUAL VIOLENCE AND HOW WE
TALK ABOUT THIS MOVEMENT.
THIS IS A MOVEMENT THAT'S ABOUT
HEALING AND ACTION.
THE HEALING AND ACTION PART OF
THAT IS BASED ON HOW WE EDUCATE
PEOPLE AROUND SEXUAL VIOLENCE.
HOW WE EDUCATE PEOPLE AROUND
WHAT SURVIVAL LOOKS LIKE.
WHEN WE SHIFT A NARRATIVE, WHEN
PEOPLE ARE MORE EDUCATED ABOUT
THIS.
THESE ARE PEOPLE WHO VOTE,
PEOPLE WHO MAKE LEGISLATIVE
DECISIONS, THEY HAVE TO
UNDERSTAND THIS CAN'T COME FROM
THIS SORT OF POP CULTURE
SALACIOUS HEADLINE PLACE.
IT HAS TO COME FROM A PLACE
WHERE THEY HAVE EMPATHY AND
UNDERSTANDING FOR WHAT SURVIVAL
IS.
>> YOU HO DO WE GET THERE,
BECAUSE YOU AND I TALKED ABOUT
THIS BEFORE WHEN THE PEOPLE
ACCUSED OF SEXUAL HARASSMENT OR
ASSAULT ARE NOT MEDIA OR
POLITICIANS OR CEOs OF MAJOR
COMPANIES, HAS THIS TRICKLED
DOWN TO HELP VICTIMS OF SEXUAL
VIOLENCE WHO DON'T HAVE A NAME,
WHO ARE HOMELESS, WHO ARE
IMMIGRANTS, WHO ARE SINGLE
MOTHERS AND WORK ON A FACTORY
FLOOR?
>> THAT'S OUR WORK.
THAT'S WHAT THE ME TOO
ORGANIZATION IS ABOUT AND WE
HAVE A LOT OF PEOPLE DOING THIS
WORK ON THE GROUND.
I'M APPRECIATIVE INTO COMING
INTO PLACES LIKE THIS AND BE
ABLE TORM TALK ABOUT IT ON A
NATIONAL FRONT.
THIS IS HOW WE CHANGE IT.
PEOPLE NEED TO UNDERSTAND THIS
WORK IS HAPPENING.
IT WAS HAPPENING BEFORE ME TOO
WENT VIRAL AND CONTINUING TO
HAPPEN.
PART OF WHAT WE DO IS EDUCATE
PEOPLE ABOUT WHAT THIS IS.
PART OF THE WORK THAT OTHER
ORGANIZATIONS DO, OTHER NATIONAL
ORGANIZATIONS, LAW CENTER AND
OTHER ORGANIZATIONS LIKE THAT
ARE EDUCATING PEOPLE BUT WE'RE
ALSO GALVANIZING PEOPLE.
PEOPLE ASK WHAT IS THE ME TOO
MOVEMENT GOING TO DO ABOUT X?
I'M SAYING WE'RE ALL THE ME TOO
MOVEMENT.
WE ALL HAVE TO BE RESPONSIVE.
WE HAVE ALL SPOB RESPONSIBLE
WHEN SOMETHING LIKE THIS HAPPENS
WE ALL HAVE TO BE OUTRAGED AND
PUSHED BACK.
HISTORICALLY JUDICIAL SYSTEMS
AND POLITICAL SYSTEMS HAVE TO
CATCH UP TO WHERE THE PEOPLE
ARE.
THE PEOPLE REALIZE STUFF LIKE
THIS IS AWFUL.
BUT WE HAVE TO PUSH BACK AND
RAISE OUR VOICES SO THE COURT
SYSTEMS KNOW AND SO THAT THE
POLITICIANS KNOW WE WON'T STAND
FOR IT.
>> WE APPRECIATE YOU COMING AND
HELPING US GET SMARTER ABOUT
THIS AND HELPING OUR AUDIENCE.
TARANA BURKE IS A FOUNDER OF THE
ME TOO MOVEMENT.
THAT WRAPS UP THIS HOUR FOR ME.
I'M BACK MONDAY AT 1:00 P.M.
EASTERN FOR "VELSHI & RUHLE
LIVE."
HAVE YOURSELVES A GREAT WEEKEND.
.
and it really shows.
With all that USAA offers
why go with anybody else?
We know
their rates are good,
we know that they're
always going to
take care of us.
It was an instant savings and
I should have changed
a long time ago.
It was funny because
when we would call
another insurance company,
hey would say
“Oh we can't beat USAA”
We're the Webber family.
We're the Tenney's
We're the Hayles,
and we're USAA members for life.
♪
Get your USAA
auto insurance quote today.
(VO)
Parents have a way of imagining
the worst...
...especially when your easily
distracted teenager has the car.
♪
At Subaru, we're taking on
distracted driving
[PING]
with sensors that alert you when
your eyes are off the road.
The all-new Subaru Forester.
The safest Forester ever.
Going to the Shawn Mendes
Verizon UP concert
was like an
out of body experience.
We were right in front of him.
Dead center. Front row.
'Cause actually, Zarmina,
you touched Shawn Mendes.
Yeah, I touched him!
She touched Shawn Mendes!
He like held my hand
for a while.
And then we got
to meet him after,
which was like...
Another surprise.
Yeah.
We love Verizon even more now.
I'll never forget
that day. Ever.
(VO)
The network more people rely on,
gives you more.
Like thousands of tickets
to concerts,
festivals and private shows.
And big savings on
our best phones when you switch.