THE WHEEL, AN AGGRESSIVE FTC
THAT WOULD WANT TO CRACK DOWN ON
SOME OF THESE THINGS THAT WARREN
LAID OUT WOULD BE SHOCKING.
>> THAT'S THE AMAZING THING
ABOUT THIS REVISED ANTITRUST
MOVEMENT.
THERE'S ALREADY REGULATORY
BODIES, STATUTORY AUTHORITY IN
PLACE.
THE CRAZIEST THING IS IT HAS NOT
BEEN USE INSTEAD A PARTICULARLY
AGGRESSIVE YEAR BECAUSE OF A
REVOLUTION IN THE WAY ALL THIS
STUFF WAS DONE.
>> I THINK THE OTHER THING AS A
SMALL BUSINESS OWNER, I CAN TELL
YOU I SEE THIS ALL THE TIME, IS
YOU SEE WHEN COMPANIES GET BIG
THE FIRST THING THEY DO IS
INCREASE THE BARRIERS OF ENTRY
TO KEEP PEOPLE LIKE ME FROM
GETTING INTO THE PROCESS.
>> AND THE STORY ELIZABETH
WARREN SAID WHILE AMAZON WILL
SIT THERE YOUR PLATES LOOK NICE,
WE'RE SELLING AMAZON PLATES NOW.
THANK YOU BOTH FOR BEING WITH ME
TONIGHT.
>> THAT IS ALL IN FOR THIS
EVENING.
THE RACHEL MADDOW SHOW STARTS
NOW.
JOY IS IN FOR RH.
>>> RACHEL HAS THE NIGHT OFF.
SHE WILL BE BACK ON MONDAY.
HAPPY FRIDAY, EVERYBODY.
YESTERDAY WE WERE TREATED TO TWO
RELATED PIECES OF NEWS THAT WERE
BOTH SHOCKING IN THEIR OWN WAY.
WE WITNESSED THE SPECTACLE OF
THE SITTING PRESIDENT'S CAMPAIGN
CHAIRPERSON BEING SENTENCED TO
PRISON, THE FIRST TIME IN U.S.
HISTORY THAT THAT HAS EVER
HAPPENED.
THAT IS THING ONE.
BUT THE SECOND PIECE WAS WHAT
KIND OF SENTENCE PAUL MANAFORT
GOT, ONE THAT SHOCKED EVEN
VETERAN PROSECUTORS BECAUSE PAUL
MANAFORT'S SENTENCE OF NEARLY
FOUR YEARS IN PRISON ON EIGHT
FELONY FINANCIAL FRAUD COUNTS
WAS FAR LESS THAN THE 19 1/2 TO
24 YEARS THAT WERE RECOMMENDED
BY THE FEDERAL SENTENCING
GUIDELINES FOR HIS CRIMES, FAR
LESS THAN WE'VE SEEN PEOPLE
SENTENCED FOR FOR ANYTHING FROM
MISTAKENLY VOTING IN AN ELECTION
WITH A PREVIOUS FELONY
CONVICTION OR BEING CONVICTED
FOR MARIJUANA POSSESSION.
FOR A LOT OF PEOPLE WATCHING
THAT SENTENCE, YESTERDAY FELT
LIKE AN OBJECT LESSON IN RICH
MAN'S JUSTICE.
AND THEN LAST NIGHT, MANAFORT'S
LAWYER EXITED THE COURTROOM WITH
A COMPLETE NON-SEQUITER TALKING
POINT THAT HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH WHAT HAPPENED IN THE COURT.
>> AS YOU HEARD IN COURT TODAY,
MR. MANAFORT FINALLY GOT TO
SPEAK FOR HIMSELF.
HE MADE CLEAR HE ACCEPTS
RESPONSIBILITY FOR HIS CONDUCT,
AND I THINK MOST IMPORTANTLY
WHAT YOU SAW TODAY IS THE SAME
THING THAT WE HAD SAID FROM DAY
ONE.
THERE IS ABSOLUTELY NO EVIDENCE
THAT PAUL MANAFORT WAS INVOLVED
WITH ANY COLLUSION WITH ANY
GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL FROM RUSSIA.
THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THE
SENTENCE?
>> THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
NO COLLUSION.
WAIT, WAIT, WHAT?
EVEN THE VERY LENIENT JUDGE WHO
SAID THAT MANAFORT HAD LED AN
OTHERWISE EXEMPLARY LIFE,
BESIDES THE EIGHT MAJOR FELONIES
THAT ROBBED THE UNITED STATES OF
TENS OF MILLIONS OF DOLLARS,
EVEN THAT JUDGE SAID EARLY ON IN
THE TRIAL THAT THE CHARGES
AGAINST MANAFORT HAD NOTHING TO
DO WITH RUSSIAN COLLUSION, SO TO
COME OUT OF THAT TRIAL SAYING
SEE THAT, NO EVIDENCE OF
COLLUSION, THAT MAKES ABOUT ZERO
SENSE.
AND THEN TODAY AS IF BY
COINCIDENCE, DONALD TRUMP PICKED
UP THAT FAMILIAR TALKING POINT
AND RAN WITH IT.
VERY POINTEDLY DIRECTING
REPORTERS TO THOSE COMMENTS FROM
MANAFORT'S LAWYER.
TRUMP SAID HE WAS, QUOTE, VERY
HONORED THAT THE JUDGE IN THE
CASE HAD DECLARED THAT THERE WAS
NO COLLUSION IN RUSSIA.
FIRST OF ALL, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THE JUDGE DID NOT SAY THAT
BECAUSE, AGAIN, THAT'S NOT WHAT
THE MANAFORT CASE WAS ABOUT, BUT
TRUMP WAS VERY HONORED BY THOSE
IMAGINARY WORDS FROM THE JUDGE.
AND DONALD TRUMP DIDN'T STOP
THERE.
HE KEPT ON STEERING THE
DISCUSSION BACK TO NO COLLUSION,
AND EVEN BACK TO HIS LONG-TIME
LAWYER MICHAEL COHEN, EVEN
THOUGH THERE IS LITERALLY
NOTHING IN THE COHEN SAGA THAT
BENEFITS HIM.
LET'S TALK ABOUT MY OTHER CLOSE
ASSOCIATE WHO'S HEADED TO PRISON
SOON, #NOCOLLUSION.
SO A COUPLE OF THINGS ARE WEIRD
ABOUT THIS, THERE'S THE FACT
THAT MANAFORT THROUGH HIS LAWYER
SEEMED TO BE PARROTING THE TRUMP
SCRIPT EVEN AS HE PREPARES TO GO
BEFORE ANOTHER JUDGE FOR A
SECOND SENTENCING, WITH A JUDGE
WHO HAS NOW ABSORBED THE MASSIVE
PUBLIC OUTRAGE ABOUT HOW SHORT A
SENTENCE HE JUST RECEIVED.
AND MORE THAN A FEW LEGAL
OBSERVERS ARE THINKING THE
REASON HE'S SINGING FROM THE
TRUMP NO COLLUSION SONG BOOK IS
PARDONS, SOMETHING TRUMP ALSO
BROUGHT UP, UNPROMPTED TODAY
ABOUT MICHAEL COHEN.
TRUMP TOLD REPORTERS TODAY THAT
COHEN LIED TO CONGRESS WHEN HE
SAID THAT HE HAD NEVER SOUGHT A
PARDON.
THEN AS SOON AS HE BOARDED HIS
PLANE FOR ALABAMA TODAY, TRUMP
TWEETED THAT MICHAEL COHEN HAD
ASKED HIM DIRECTLY FOR A PARDON,
AND TRUMP CLAIMED HE SAID NO.
NOW COHEN SAYS THAT TRUMP IS
LYING ABOUT THAT BUT REPUBLICAN
CONGRESSMAN JIM JORDAN SAID HE'S
GOINGS TO SEND ANOTHER CRIMINAL
REFERRAL TO THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT OVER COHEN'S ALLEGED
LIE ABOUT WHETHER HE ASKED FOR A
PARDON RAISING THE FOLLOW
INTRIGUING QUESTION.
WILL DONALD TRUMP HAVE TO BE
INTERVIEWED AS PART OF AN
INVESTIGATION INTO MICHAEL
COHEN'S ALLEGED LYING ABOUT
TRYING FOR A PARDON?
I MEAN, IF THEY HAD A ONE ON ONE
CONVERSATION ABOUT IT AS DONALD
TRUMP ALLEGES IN HIS TWITTER
FEED, WOULDN'T TRUMP HAVE TO
GIVE EVIDENCE?
ALSO TODAY, WHITE HOUSE
COMMUNICATIONS DIRECTOR BILL
SHINE ABRUPTLY RESIGNED.
BILL SHINE CAME TO THE WHITE
HOUSE FROM FOX NEWS, AND HE WILL
NOW GO TO WORK ON DONALD TRUMP'S
RE-ELECTION CAMPAIGN, PERHAPS
ONE DAY HE'LL END UP BACK AT FOX
NEWS.
AH, YES, IT'S THE CIRCLE OF
LIFE.
AND SPEAKING OF WHITE HOUSE
COMMUNICATIONS, ONE OF THE
THINGS THAT HAS MADE THIS WHITE
HOUSE DIFFERENT FROM ALL THE
OTHER WHITE HOUSES IS THE AMOUNT
OF LEAKING THAT HAPPENS INSIDE
IT.
THIS WHITE HOUSE IS SO LEAKY
LAST YEAR "AXIOS" PUBLISHED A
PIECE ENTITLED WHITE HOUSE
LEAKERS LEAK ABOUT LEAKING, IN
WHICH SOME OF THE
ADMINISTRATION'S MOST PROLIFIC
ANONYMOUS LEAKERS SPOKE TO
"AXIOS" ANONYMOUSLY ABOUT WHAT
THEY LEAK AND WHY, AND WHEN IT
COMES TO WHITE HOUSE LEAKING,
THERE'S THE PETTY SCORE SETTLING
KIND.
THERE'S THE KIND DESIGNED TO
ADVANCE YOUR PREFERRED POLICY
POSITION IF YOU'VE LOST SOME
INTERNAL DEBATE, AND IN THIS
WHITE HOUSE, THERE'S EVEN
LEAKING BECAUSE MAYBE YOU THINK
THE ONLY WAY TO REACH THE
PRESIDENT IS TO GET SOMETHING
ONTO THE TV SO THAT HE CAN SEE
IT DURING HIS EXECUTIVE TIME.
THERE'S ALSO LEAKING OUT OF
CONCERN, LEAKING THAT APPEARS TO
BE UNDERTAKEN TO SOUND THE
ALARM.
IT WAS SIX MONTHS AGO THIS WEEK
THAT WE GOT THE ASTONISHING
OP-ED IN THE "NEW YORK TIMES" IN
WHICH AN ANONYMOUS SENIOR TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION OFFICIAL
DESCRIBED BEING ONE OF A NUMBER
OF SENIOR ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIALS, QUOTE, WORKING
DILIGENTLY FROM WITHIN TO
FRUSTRATE PARTS OF TRUMP'S
AGENDA AND HIS WORST
INCLINATIONS.
QUOTE, WE BELIEVE OUR FIRST DUTY
IS TO THIS COUNTRY, AND THE
PRESIDENT CONTINUES TO ACT IN A
MANNER THAT IS DETRIMENTAL TO
THE HEALTH OF OUR REPUBLICAN.
AMERICANS SHOULD KNOW THAT THERE
ARE ADULTS IN THE ROOM.
WE ARE TRYING TO DO WHAT'S
RIGHT, EVEN WHEN DONALD TRUMP
WON'T.
NOW, YOUR MILEAGE MAY VARY AS TO
WHETHER YOU THOUGHT THAT OP-ED
WAS COURAGEOUS OR
SELF-JUSTIFYING, REASSURING OR
TERRIFYING.
IT WAS THE KIND OF LEAK FROM
INSIDE THIS ADMINISTRATION.
HERE'S SOMETHING I THINK THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE SHOULD KNOW
ABOUT WHAT'S HAPPENING HERE.
THERE HAVE BEEN A NUMBER OF OF
THESE, AT THE BEGINNING OF
TRUMP'S PRESIDENCY ANONYMOUS
WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS LEAKED
DETAILS AND TRANSCRIPTS OF
TRUMP'S PHONE CALLS WITH FOREIGN
LEADERS.
SURE, MAYBE THEY DID THAT TO
EMBARRASS HIM, BUT IT SEEMED
THAT SOME PEOPLE INSIDE THIS
WHITE HOUSE THOUGHT THE PUBLIC
NEEDED TO KNOW WHAT TRUMP WAS
SAYING ON THOSE CALLS.
THERE WAS THE REPORT A FEW
MONTHS AGO THAT THE PRESIDENT
WAS CARRYING ON ALL KINDS OF
SENSITIVE CONVERSATIONS WITH
FRIENDS ON HIS UNSECURED CELL
PHONE.
CONVERSATIONS BEING LISTENED TO
BY CHINESE AND RUSSIAN
INTELLIGENCE.
THAT LEAK CERTAINLY SOUNDS LIKE
A WARNING OR MAYBE A CRY FOR
HELP, QUOTE, MR. TRUMP'S AIDES
HAVE REPEATEDLY WARNED HIM THAT
HIS CELL PHONE CALLS ARE NOT
SECURE, AND THEY HAVE TOLD HIM
THAT RUSSIAN SPIES ARE ROUTINELY
EAVESDROPPING ON THE CALLS, BUT
AIDES SAY THE VOLUBLE PRESIDENT
HAS STILL REFUSED TO GIVE UP HIS
iPHONES.
WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS SAY THEY
CAN ONLY HOPE HE REFRAINS FROM
DISCUSSING CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION WHEN HE WAS ON THEM.
WE HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO GET HIM
TO DO THAT DANGEROUS THING, SO
WE BETTER ALERT THE PUBLIC ABOUT
IT THOSE LEAKED SEEMED TO SAY.
AND THERE HAVE BEEN LEAKS ABOUT
JARED KUSHNER AND HIS SECURITY
CLEARANCE, THAT HE HAD AN
INTERIM CLEARANCE FOR A YEAR
BECAUSE OFFICIALS WOULD NOT
CLEAR HIM FOR A PERMANENT ONE.
AND THEN HIS INTERIM CLEARANCE
WAS REVOKED, AND THEN THE
PRESIDENT REPORTEDLY ORDERED
THAT HE BE GIVEN A TOP SECURITY
CLEARANCE DESPITE ALL THE RED
FLAGS THAT WERE RAISED BY
INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS, AND THE
PRESIDENT'S CHIEF OF STAFF AND
WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL BEING SO
ALARMED BY THE PRESIDENT'S
DECISION THAT THEY BOTH WROTE
CONTEMPORANEOUS MEMOS
DOCUMENTING WHY THEY THOUGHT
JARED KUSHNER SHOULD NEVER HAVE
GOTTEN A CLEARANCE.
AND YES, SOMEONE IN THE
ADMINISTRATION WHO HAS A BEEF
WITH JARED MAY BE LEAKING THIS
STUFF TO UNDERCUT HIM.
THAT IS CERTAINLY POSSIBLE, BUT
THIS IS ALSO SOMEONE SOUNDING AN
ALARM THAT THIS GUY IS HAVING A
LOT OF TROUBLE GETTING A
SECURITY CLEARANCE FOR A REASON,
AND LIKE I SAID, WE ARE USED TO
THESE LEAKS TO THE MEDIA.
EVERY DAY IT SEEMS WE GET AT
LEAST ONE.
BUT TODAY WE GOT A SIGNAL THAT
THERE MAY BE A SUBSTANTIAL SHIFT
UNDERWAY IN THE NATURE AND THE
SERIOUSNESS OF THESE
DISCLOSURES, A SHIFT THAT HAS
ALL KINDS OF IMPLICATIONS FOR
OVERSIGHT AND FOR INVESTIGATIONS
OF THIS WHITE HOUSE.
THE HOUSE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE
HAS BEEN ASKING THE WHITE HOUSE
FOR DOCUMENTS ON THE SECURITY
CLEARANCE ISSUE FOR WEEKS, EVER
SINCE DEMOCRATS TOOK OVER THE
COMMITTEE, AND THIS WEEK THE
WHITE HOUSE FINALLY SAID NO.
NO DOCUMENTS, WHICH WAS EXPECTED
TO TRIGGER A SUBPOENA FROM THE
COMMITTEE AND THEN POSSIBLY A
BIG HUGE FIGHT OVER THAT
SUBPOENA.
WELL, TODAY "AXIOS" REPORTS THAT
THE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE HAS
ALREADY GOTTEN ITS HANDS ON A
NUMBER OF THE DOCUMENTS.
THEY WERE LEAKED TO THE
COMMITTEE BY SOMEONE INSIDE THE
WHITE HOUSE, QUOTE, THE HOUSE
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE IN EARLY
FEBRUARY HAD ALREADY OBTAINED
THE LEAKED DOCUMENTS, THAT
DETAIL THE ENTIRE PROCESS FROM
THE SPRING OF 2017 TO THE SPRING
OF 2018 ON HOW BOTH JARED
KUSHNER AND IVANKA TRUMP WERE
ULTIMATELY GRANTED THEIR
SECURITY CLEARANCES.
HMM, THINK ABOUT THAT.
LEAKING DAMAGING INVESTIGATION
OR SOUND THE ALARM TYPE OF
INFORMATION TO THE PRESS IS ONE
THING.
LEAKING DOCUMENTS WITH NATIONAL
SECURITY IMPLICATIONS TO A
CONGRESSIONAL COMMITTEE
CONTROLLED BY THE OPPOSITION
PARTY WITH BROAD INVESTIGATORY
AND SUBPOENA POWER, IF THIS
REPORT IS CORRECT, WE MAY BE IN
A WHOLE NEW BALL GAME.
JOINING ME NOW IS CONGRESSMAN RO
KHANNA WHO SITS ON THE OVERSIGHT
COMMITTEE.
CONGRESSMAN, THANKS SO MUCH FOR
JOINING US.
>> JOY, IT'S GOOD TO BE ON.
>> LET'S GO AND GET INTO THIS
LEAK.
OBVIOUSLY NOW THE COMMITTEE HAS
THE DOCUMENTS THAT WALK YOUR
COMMITTEE THROUGH THE PROCESS OF
HOW JARED KUSHNER AND IVANKA
TRUMP GOT THEIR SECURITY
CLEARANCES.
WHAT NOW DOES THE COMMITTEE WANT
TO DO ABOUT IT?
IS THIS GOING TO TRIGGER
HEARINGS, AND COULD WE SEE
IVANKA TRUMP AND JARED KUSHNER
FORCED TO TESTIFY OR WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIALS WHO GRANTED THEM THEIR
CLEARANCES?
>> JOY, LET ME EXPLAIN WHY THIS
IS SUCH A BIG DEAL.
FOR A PRESIDENT WHO SPENT THE
ENTIRE 2016 CAMPAIGN TRAIL
RAILING AGAINST HILLARY
CLINTON'S PRIVATE E-MAIL
SERVERS, THIS IS A FAR BIGGER
NATIONAL SECURITY CRISIS.
THERE ARE ALLEGATIONS THAT JARED
KUSHNER HAD SENSITIVE
INFORMATION THAT HE HAS
ALLEGEDLY BEEN GIVING LISTS TO
MBS, THE SAUDI CROWN PRINCE
ABOUT SAUDI DISSIDENCE, THAT
HE'S BEEN ON WHATSAPP WITH SAUDI
ARABIA'S CROWN PRINCE, AND WE
NEED TO KNOW WHAT IS IT THAT'S
IN HIS BACKGROUND THAT WAS
CAUSING CONCERN.
HAS HE BEEN SHARING SENSITIVE
TOP SECRET INFORMATION WITH
PEOPLE IN SAUDI ARABIA OR OTHER
COUNTRIES?
WHY IS IT THAT HE HAS NOT
DISCLOSED A NUMBER OF HIS
FOREIGN BUSINESS RELATIONS.
THIS IS NOT A PARTISAN ISSUE.
IT'S NOT A BUREAUCRATIC ISSUE.
THIS IS OUR MOST SENSITIVE
INFORMATION THAT MAY BE GETTING
INTO THE WRONG HANDS.
>> AND CAN I ASK YOU, DOES THE
COMMITTEE HAS THE
CONTEMPORANEOUS NOTES THAT JOHN
KELLY, THE FORMER CHIEF OF STAFF
AND THE WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL DON
McGAHN WROTE ABOUT THESE TWO
OBTAINING THESE CLEARANCES?
DO YOU ALL HAVE THESE NOTES?
>> I DON'T THINK WE HAVE THOSE
YET, BUT AS YOU POINTED OUT,
BOTH JOHN KELLY AND THE WHITE
HOUSE COUNSEL AT THE TIME WERE
OPPOSED TO THE DECISION TO GIVE
JARED KUSHNER TOP SECRET
CLEARANCE.
THEY WERE SO OPPOSED TO IT THAT
THEY FELT THE NEED TO WRITE A
MEMO DOCUMENTING HOW CONCERNED
THEY WERE AND WHY JARED KUSHNER
SHOULDN'T BE GET THIS
INFORMATION.
THIS HAS IMPLICATIONS ABOUT OUR
POLICY IN THE MIDDLE EAST.
I MEAN, THE PRESIDENT HAS MADE
JARED KUSHNER THE POINT PERSON
ON MIDDLE EAST PEACE OR MIDDLE
EAST POLICY, AND WE NEED TO KNOW
WHAT INFORMATION HE HAS AND WHO
IS HE SHARING IT WITH.
>> AND IN THE DOCUMENTS THAT
WERE LEAKED TO THE COMMITTEE, IS
THERE ANYTHING IN THOSE
DOCUMENTS THAT INDICATES TO YOU
THAT JARED KUSHNER MIGHT HAVE
SHARED CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
WITH THE SAUDI PRINCE?
>> I CAN'T SAY IT'S IN THAT, BUT
THERE HAS BEEN PUBLIC REPORTING
ON A NUMBER OF KEY POINTS.
ONE, THAT JARED KUSHNER HAD
ACCESS TO THE PRESIDENTS' DAILY
BRIEF.
IN THAT DAILY BRIEF WERE
NUMEROUS REPORTS ABOUT SAUDI
DISSIDENTS AND HE ALLEGEDLY
SHARED THAT LIST WITH THE SAUDI
CROWN PRINCE.
SECOND, JARED KUSHNER HAS HAD
MEETINGS WITH THE SAUDI PRINCE
WITHOUT HAVING ANYONE IN OUR
EMBASSY THERE.
THAT IS NOT STANDARD PROTOCOL.
WE KNOW THE CROWN PRINCE MOST
LIKELY ORDERED THE KILLING OF
KHASHOGGI.
WE KNOW HIS ORDERING THE BOMBING
OF HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF
CIVILIANS IN YEMEN, AND HERE
THERE ARE SERIOUS ALLEGATIONS OF
WHAT JARED KUSHNER IS SHARING
WITH HIM.
THIS IS NOT A BUREAUCRATIC
ISSUE.
THIS IS A HUGELY SENSITIVE ISSUE
ABOUT THE HIGHEST NATIONAL
SECURITY OF THIS COUNTRY.
>> AND WE KNOW JUST FROM PUBLIC
REPORTING THAT ONE OF THE
CHALLENGES THAT JARED KUSHNER
LIKELY HAD GET AGO CLEARANCE WAS
THE FACT THAT HE WAS IN A LOT OF
DEBT.
HE HAD A BUILDING HERE IN
MANHATTAN THAT HAD A BIG BALLOON
PAYMENT DUE.
HIS FATHER WAS REPORTEDLY
LOOKING -- HELPING HIM TO LOOK
FOR WAYS TO PAY THAT BILL.
HAVE YOU FOUND IN ANYTHING OF
THOSE LEAKED DOCUMENTS, ANY OF
THOSE LEAKED DOCUMENTS, ANYTHING
THAT WOULD INDICATE TO YOU THAT
JARED KUSHNER WAS SEEKING
FUNDING, SEEKING MONEY FROM THE
MIDDLE EAST WHILE HE WAS IN THE
MIDDLE EAST PURPORTEDLY
NEGOTIATING ON BEHALF OF THE
UNITED STATES?
>> I CAN'T COMMENT ON THOSE
DOCUMENTS, BUT JUST IN GENERAL,
THE PUBLIC REPORTING THERE ARE
HUGE REPORTS THAT JARED KUSHNER
HASN'T BEEN FULLY FORTHCOMING
ABOUT ALL OF HIS OVERSEAS
BUSINESS DEALINGS AND ALL OF HIS
FOREIGN CONTACTS.
YOU KNOW, I HAD A SECURITY
BACKGROUND CHECK WHEN I WORKED
AT THE COMMERCE DEPARTMENT.
YOU HAVE TO DISCLOSE EVERY
SINGLE PERSON YOU'VE EVER MET
WITH IN A FOREIGN COUNTRY IN THE
PAST SEVEN YEARS, AND FOR
KUSHNER NOT TO HAVE DISCLOSED
FINANCIAL TRANSACTIONS OR HIS
OVERSEES CONTACTS PUTS HIM AND
THE COUNTRY IN A VULNERABLE
SPOT.
IT MAY NOT HAVE BEEN SOMETHING
HE REALIZED PUT HIM IN A
VULNERABLE SPOT.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE THESE
BACKGROUND CHECKS TO SEE IF
SOMEONE COULD TAKE ADVANTAGE OF
HIM.
AND I HAVE CONCERNS WHETHER THE
SAUDIS HAVE BEEN TAKEN ADVANTAGE
OF THE SITUATION.
>> CONGRESSMAN, THANK YOU SO
MUCH.
REALLY APPRECIATE YOUR TIME
TONIGHT.
>> JOY, THANKS FOR HAVING ME
BACK ON.
>> IF THIS REPORT TODAY FROM
"AXIOS" IS ACCURATE THAT SOMEONE
INSIDE THE WHITE HOUSE HAS
LEAKED DOCUMENTS TO THE HOUSE
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE ABOUT HOW
JARED KUSHNER AND IVANKA TRUMP
GOT THEIR SECURITY CLEARANCES,
DOCUMENTS THE WHITE HOUSE HAS
BEEN REFUSING TO HAND OVER TO
THAT COMMITTEE, HOW BIG A CHANGE
IS THAT FROM THE RUN-OF-THE-MILL
LEAKS TO THE PRESS THAT WE'VE
ALL GOTTEN ACCUSTOMED TO.
HOW WORRIED SHOULD THE WHITE
HOUSE BE?
>> JOINING US NOW IS MICHAEL
BESH LATCH.
>> HOW UNPRECEDENTED IS IT FOR
THE WHITE HOUSE TO HAND OVER
DOCUMENTS OF THIS SENSITIVE
NATURE AND HAVE SOMEONE IN THE
WHITE HOUSE LEAK IT TO A
CONGRESSIONAL COMMITTEE?
>> THAT'S THE THING, ANYONE
WHO'S COMPLAINING THAT THE TRUMP
WHITE HOUSE IS NOT FULL OF
INNOVATIONS, HERE IS ONE OF
THEM, WHICH IS USUALLY YOU SEE
SOMEONE IN THE WHITE HOUSE
LEAKING SOMETHING TO THE PRESS,
AND IF THERE'S AN INVESTIGATION
IN CONGRESS, THE COMMITTEE USES
IT.
THE TRUMP WHITE HOUSE, IF THAT
IS THE SOURCE OF THESE
DOCUMENTS, HAS NOW CUT OUT THE
MIDDLE PERSON.
YOU KNOW, JOY, MAYBE TWO OF THE
BIGGEST REVELATIONS OF
GOVERNMENT SECRETS IN THE LAST
50 YEARS WERE THE PENTAGON
PAPERS AND THE NIXON TAPES.
THE PENTAGON PAPERS WERE LEAKED
BY A FORMER PENTAGON EMPLOYEE
DANIEL ELSBERG TO THE "NEW YORK
TIMES" AND "THE WASHINGTON POST"
BECAUSE HE FELT THIS WAS
SOMETHING AMERICANS NEEDED TO
SEE, HOW WE GOT INTO THIS
CATASTROPHIC VIETNAM WAR.
AND THE NIXON TAPES, THAT WAS
ONE OF THE MOST CLOSELY HELD
SECRETS IN THE NIXON WHITE
HOUSE.
A MEMBER OF THE SENATE WATERGATE
COMMITTEE STAFF BASICALLY GUESS
THAT HAD PERHAPS NIXON WAS
TAPING HIS PRIVATE CONVERSATIONS
AND ASKED A SERVING WHITE HOUSE
AIDE ALEXANDER BUTTERFIELD.
THAT'S THE TRADITIONAL WAY, VERY
DIFFERENT FROM WHAT WE'RE SEEING
NOW WITH THESE DOCUMENTS FROM
THE TRUMP WHITE HOUSE.
>> JUST TO TAKE IT FURTHER
AFIELD, RIGHT, IF DONALD TRUMP,
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES ORDERED THESE SECURITY
CLEARANCES TO BE GRANTED OVER
THE OBJECTIONS OF HIS NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISERS, NATIONAL
SECURITY STAFF, ULYSSES S.
GRANTED TESTIFIED IN THE WHISKEY
RING SCANDAL, RIGHT, THERE IS A
PRECEDENT OF A PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES GIVING TESTIMONY
TO A SPECIAL PROSECUTOR, NO
LESS.
>> OH, SURE.
>> COULD YOU SEE TRUMP HAVE TO
DO THAT?
>> GERALD FORD TESTIFIED BEFORE
THE HOUSE SAYING THERE WAS NO
DEAL LEADING TO THE NIXON
PARDON.
HE DID THAT IN THE FALL OF 1974:
THERE SURE IS.
SO SOME OF THESE OLD TRADITIONS,
EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE IS A
TRADITION.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT'S IN THE
CONSTITUTION.
>> AND LASTLY, IS THERE AN
ANTECEDENT TO A JARED KUSHNER,
SOMEONE WHO HAD SO MUCH DEBT,
AND WAS IN A POSITION TO READ
THE PRESIDENTS' DAILY BRIEF.
>> AND IF HE USED HIS POSITION,
IF HE DID TO ESSENTIALLY
COMPROMISE OUR AMERICAN SECURITY
INTERESTS IN ORDER TO GET MONEY
TO BAIL OUT HIS FAMILY IN THAT
BUILDING, THAT IS SOMETHING THAT
WE HAVE NEVER SEEN BEFORE, AND
YOU HAVE TO ASSUME THAT WHOEVER
LEAKED THIS, IF THIS IS SOMEONE
IN THE WHITE HOUSE, FELT THAT
THIS WAS SUCH AN OUTRAGE AND
THERE WAS SUCH A DANGER THAT
THERE MIGHT BE FUTURE SUCH
BEHAVIOR IF JARED KUSHNER OR HIS
WIFE HAD TOP SECURITY CLEARANCES
THAT THEY WOULD BE A CLEAR AND
PRESENT DANGER.
WE'VE GOT TO LOOK AT THIS AS A
CRY FOR HELP.
>> IT'S ALL EXTRAORDINARY.
NEW HISTORICAL RECORDS BEING SET
EVERY DAY.
THANK YOU, SIR, REALLY
APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANK YOU, JOY.
SEE YOU SOON.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> STILL AHEAD TONIGHT, LITTLE
COURT TRANSCRIPT THEATER, GO GET
YOUR POPCORN.
I'LL WAIT RIGHT HERE, AND WE'LL
BE RIGHT BACK.
L
e.
Why accept it from
your allergy pills?
Flonase Sensimist relieves
all your worst symptoms,
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
And all from a gentle mist
you can barely feel.
Flonase Sensimist.
SARAH'S LAST TUITION
PAYMENT, SENT OFF.
FEELING GOOD?
OH YEAH.
NOW I'M READY TO
FOCUS ON MY PROJECT.
♪ ♪ ♪
THIS IS WHY WE PLAN.
YOU NEVER CEASE
TO AMAZE ME, MAYA.
SEE HOW INVESTING WITH A J.P.
MORGAN ADVISOR CAN HELP YOU.
VISIT YOUR LOCAL CHASE BRANCH.
Termites,
feasting on homes 24/7.
We're on the move.
Roger.
Hey Rick, all good?
Oh yeah, we're good.
We're good.
Termites never stop trying to
get in,
we never stop working to keep
them out.
Terminix.
Defenders of Home.
>>> WE NOW KNOW FROM THE
TRANSCRIPT OF YESTERDAY'S PAUL
MANAFORT SENTENCING THAT MOMENTS
AFTER THE JUDGE HANDED DOWN HIS
FATE MANAFORT'S DEFENSE TEAM
MADE ONE LAST BRAZEN APPEAL.
SPECIFICALLY MANAFORT LAWYER
KEVIN DOWNING ASKED JUDGE T.S.
ELLIS IF HE COULD ORDER -- AND I
DID SAY ORDER -- THAT THE
SENTENCE HE HAD JUST ISSUED BE
SERVED CONCURRENTLY WITH
WHATEVER SENTENCE THE JUDGE IN
HIS D.C. CASE ISSUES NEXT WEEK.
NOW HERE'S THE TRANSCRIPT.
I CANNOT DO THIS AS WELL AS
RACHEL BUT GO WITH ME ON THIS,
QUOTE, YOUR HONOR THERE IS ONE
OTHER ISSUE WE'D LIKE TO RAISE,
MANAFORT'S LAWYER TOLD THE
JUDGE.
IT HAS TO DO WITH WHETHER OR NOT
YOU CAN ORDER THIS SENTENCE TO
BE CONCURRENTLY SERVED WITH --
AT WHICH POINT THE JUDGE
INTERRUPTS HIM TO SAY -- QUOTE,
I CAN'T BUT SHE CAN.
I DON'T BELIEVE I CAN IF YOU
FIND IN THE LAW THAT I'M
INCORRECT, YOU CAN BRING THAT TO
MY ATTENTION.
THE JUDGE THEN ADDS I THINK IT
IS ENTIRELY UP TO HER WHETHER
ANY SENTENCE SHE IMPOSES IS TO
RUN CONCURRENT TO THIS SENTENCE.
IT'S UP TO HER.
ANYTHING ELSE, MR. DOWNING?
TO WHICH MANAFORT'S LAWYER
REPLIED, NO YOUR HONOR.
WHICH IS A MORE DIPLOMATIC WAY
OF SAYING OF COURSE NOT.
I MEAN, IT TAKES A SPECIAL LEVEL
OF RICH GUY PRIVILEGE TO THINK
THAT YOU COULD ASK THE JUDGE,
WHO JUST CUT YOU A MASSIVE
BREAK, TO MAKE SURE THAT THE
NEXT JUDGE MAKES THAT BREAK
STICK.
SO CLEARLY THERE'S NO SENSE OF
CONTRITION OR REMORSE FROM
MANAFORT'S CAMP, LIKE NONE, BUT
RATHER A PRETTY BOLD PRESUMPTION
THAT THE SYSTEM SHOULD AND WILL
CONTINUE TO WORK FOR HIM.
NEXT WEEK MANAFORT WILL BE IN
COURT BEFORE JUDGE AMY BERMAN
JACKSON WHO FIRST ORDERED
MANAFORT TO JAIL FOR TAMPERING
WITH WITNESSES WHO COULD TACK ON
AS MUCH AS TEN YEARS TO THE FOUR
THAT HE'S ALREADY FACING BEHIND
BARS.
MANAFORT'S ULTIMATE FATE NEXT
WEEK COMES AS THE PROSPECT OF
MUELLER'S REPORT LOOMS OVER
EVERYTHING.
TODAY THE TOP REPUBLICAN ON THE
HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE SAID
THAT HE MET RECENTLY WITH
ATTORNEY GENERAL BILL BARR AND
PREDICTED THAT THE PUBLIC MAY
ONLY GET A SHORT SUMMARY OF
MUELLER'S FINDINGS.
GREAT.
THIS IS ALL FINE.
HIS REMARKS TODAY COME AS THE
DEMOCRATIC CHAIRS OF SIX HOUSE
COMMITTEES INTRODUCED A
RESOLUTION THAT WHEN COMPLETED
THE MUELLER REPORT SHOULD BE
MADE AVAILABLE TO THE PUBLIC AND
TO CONGRESS.
JOINING ME NOW IS DAVID CORN,
WASHINGTON BUREAU CHIEF AND
CHUCK ROSENBERG FORMER U.S.
ATTORNEY FROM VIRGINIA.
DAVID AND CHUCK, I APPRECIATE
YOUR TIME.
CHUCK, I'M GOING TO GO TO YOU
FIRST TO ASK HOW UNUSUAL IT IS,
JUST FROM YOUR POINT OF VIEW,
FOR A DEFENDANT WHO WAS JUST
SENTENCED TO SAY TO THE JUDGE,
HEY, JUDGE, CAN YOU MAKE THE
NEXT JUDGE MAKE THE SENTENCE
CONCURRENT SO THAT I CAN HAVE
LESS TIME?
LIKE IS THAT NORMAL AT ALL?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, JOY, I WAS A
PROSECUTOR FOR A LONG TIME IN
FEDERAL COURT, AND DEFENSE
ATTORNEYS ASK FOR ALL CRAZY
THINGS.
THIS ONE IS AN EASY ONE.
THERE'S A FEDERAL STATUTE RIGHT
ON POINT.
I'M GOING TO BE A LITTLE BIT OF
A NERD HERE, BUT IF YOUR VIEWERS
WANT TO READ IT'S TITLE 18 OF
THE UNITED STATES CODE SECTION
3584.
THE SIMPLE ANSWER IS NO.
THE NEXT JUDGE, AMY BERMAN
JACKSON GETS TO RUN THE SENTENCE
CONSECUTIVELY IF SHE WANTS OR
CONCURRENT IF SHE WANTS OR SOME
COMBINATION OF THE TWO.
I'VE SEEN LOTS AND LOTS OF
DEFENSE ATTORNEYS ASK FOR THINGS
THEY KNOW THEY CAN'T HAVE, AND
THE JUDGE WAS RIGHT IN THIS CASE
TO SAY NOT IN MY COURT, NOT IN
MY JURISDICTION.
I DON'T HAVE THE AUTHORITY TO
GIVE YOU WHAT YOU'RE ASKING FOR.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE SHOCKED
BY HOW LITTLE TIME THAT MANAFORT
WAS GIVEN FOR THIS SENTENCE,
THIS STUFF ABOUT HIM LEADING AN
EXEMPLARY LIFE.
WE KNOW WHAT HIS LIFE WAS BEFORE
HAND.
WERE YOU EQUALLY SHOCKED BY IT,
AND DO YOU THINK THAT THAT SHOCK
AND OUTRAGE THAT PEOPLE FELT
AROUND THE COUNTRY WILL IMPACT
JUDGE AMY BERMAN JACKSON'S
DECISION?
DO JUDGES REACT TO THE PUBLIC
REACTION TO OTHER SENTENCES?
>> YOU KNOW, THEY PROBABLY TRY
NOT TO, BUT THEY'RE HUMAN BEING
LIKE ALL OF US AND INEVITABLY
SHE SAW WHAT JUDGE ELLIS DID IN
VIRGINIA AND HAD SOME SORT OF
REACTION TO IT, I'M SURE IN HER
OWN MIND, PROBABLY ALREADY
HAVING READ, JOY, THE
PRESENTENCE REPORT FROM MR.
MANAFORT IN HER COURT.
SHE HAS AN IDEA OF WHAT SHE
THINKS IS THE JUST OUTCOME HERE.
WAS I SHOCKED?
NOT ENTIRELY.
I'VE PRACTICED IN FRONT OF JUDGE
ELLIS FOR MANY YEARS AS A
FEDERAL PROSECUTOR.
WAS I DISAPPOINTED?
I WAS DEEPLY DISAPPOINTED.
I THINK IT WAS THE WRONG CALL, A
BAD CALL.
HERE'S WHY.
MANY, MANY YEARS AGO CONGRESS
PASSED A STATUTE TO CREATE
FEDERAL SENTENCING GUIDELINES TO
BRING SOME PARODY -- PARITY INTO
THE SYSTEM, SO SOMEBODY DID WHAT
MANAFORT DID IN TOPEKA OR
WHEREVER WOULD GET ROUGHLY THE
SAME SENTENCE REGARDLESS OF
WHICH COURT WAS HANDLING THE
MATTER.
THIS WAS NOT JUST A DEPARTURE,
THIS WAS A DRAMATIC DEPARTURE,
AND IT WAS A DEPARTURE WITHOUT A
MOTIVE FROM THE GOVERNMENT.
NORMALLY IF SOMEONE HELPS THE
GOVERNMENT, THE GOVERNMENT WILL
MOVE THE COURT, ASK THE COURT TO
DEPART DOWNWARD.
MANAFORT DID NOT HELP, HE LIED.
HE DID NOT EARN A DEPARTURE.
HE CERTAINLY WAS NOT ENTITLED TO
WHAT HE GOT.
HE GOT A REAL LUCKY BREAK IN
FRONT OF JUDGE ELLIS.
I DON'T THINK THE SAME THING IS
GOING TO HAPPEN NEXT WEEK.
>> THAT'S PART OF WHAT'S
OUTRAGEOUS ABOUT THIS.
YOU HAVE MICHAEL COHEN OUT HERE
BEARING HIS SOUL IN FRONT OF
CONGRESS AND GOING BACK OVER AND
OVER AGAIN WITHOUT A DEAL.
HE KNOWS HE'S GETTING THREE
YEARS REGARDLESS.
MAYBE HE'LL GET A BREAK DOWN THE
ROAD.
MANAFORT WASN'T A GUY WHO WAS
HELPING THE GOVERNMENT.
AS A MATTER OF FACT HE WAS
OBSTRUCTING THE GOVERNMENT'S
ATTEMPT TO FIND THE TRUTH HERE,
TAMPERING WITH WITNESSES, ALL
THE OTHER THINGS HE DID.
JUST PREVIEW FOR ME -- I GUESS
NOT THE OPTICS IS THE WRONG
WORD, I FEEL BUT IF IN THE END
THIS MAN WHO DID NOT HELP, THEN
THE MUELLER REPORT COMES OUT AND
WE DON'T EVEN GET TO SEE IT,
WHAT ARE WE LEFT WITH HERE AS A
COUNTRY AFTER HAVING GONE
THROUGH THREE YEARS OF THIS.
>> THAT WON'T BE THE END OF IT,
OKAY?
I'M A LITTLE BIT FRUSTRATED,
JOY, BECAUSE PEOPLE SEEM TO BE
PUTTING ALL THEIR EGGS IN THE
MUELLER REPORT BASKET, AND
MUELLER HAS NO OBLIGATION UNDER
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
GUIDELINES TO PRODUCE A
COMPREHENSIVE REPORT TELLING,
STATING WHAT HE FOUND OUT AND
WHAT HE LEARNED.
HIS ONLY OBLIGATION IS TO GIVE A
REPORT AT THE VERY END TO THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL EXPLAINING WHY
HE PROSECUTED CASES OR DECLINED
TO PROSECUTE OTHER CASES.
YOU KNOW, IT COULD EASILY BE A
12-PAGE REPORT, YOU KNOW,
WITHOUT GETTING INTO DETAILS, OR
IF HE CHOSE TO, IT COULD BE A
5,000 PAGE REPORT EXPLAINING
EVERYTHING HE FOUND AND WHY HE
DECIDED TO PROSECUTE OR NOT
PROSECUTE.
WE DON'T KNOW, SO IT MAY WELL BE
AT THE END OF THE DAY IF IT'S A
MORE LIMITED REPORT, THERE MAY
NOT BE MUCH TO SHOW.
THIS GETS BACK TO A POINT THAT I
KNOW YOU AND I HAVE DISCUSSED
PREVIOUSLY.
IT'S NOT HIS JOB TO TELL
AMERICANS THE TRUTH.
THAT'S NOT WHAT HE WAS HIRED TO
DO.
HE WAS HIRED TO PROSECUTE, LOOK
FOR AND THEN PROSECUTE CRIMINAL
CASES.
IT'S CONGRESS'S JOB, AND WE ARE
MAYBE AN INDEPENDENT COMMISSION
TO DIG INTO ALL OF THIS AND TELL
US WHAT HAPPENED WITH TRUMP
RUSSIA CONNECTIONS AND
EVERYTHING ELSE AND THE RUSSIAN
INTERVENTION BECAUSE A LOT OF
PROBABLY WHAT WENT ON MAY NOT
HAVE BEEN A CRIME.
IT COULD BE JUST WRONG.
YOU CAN HAVE SCANDALS THAT
AREN'T NECESSARILY ILLEGAL BUT
THEY STILL CAN CONTAIN ACTS OF
PROFOUND BETRAYAL.
SO YOU KNOW, WE STILL HAVE THE
HOUSE DEMOCRATS HAVE TAKEN
CONTROL OF THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE AND ARE GOING BACK
OVER AN INVESTIGATION THAT THE
REPUBLICANS TURNED INTO A CLOWN
SHOW, AND SO THERE'S THAT, AND
HOPEFULLY THEY WILL GIVE US SOME
DEEPER AND WIDER ANSWERS THAN
ROBERT MUELLER WAS EVER ASKED TO
DO.
>> BUT YOU KNOW, DAVID MY
FRIEND, YOU AND I BOTH KNOW THAT
WHAT THE DEMOCRATS ARE SAYING
PUBLICLY, WHAT YOU'RE HEARING IN
THE REPORTING IS THAT THEY ARE
HANGING EVERYTHING ON THE
MUELLER REPORT.
THAT THEY DON'T EVEN WANT TO
TALK ABOUT IMPEACHMENT, WHICH IS
THE HEARINGS THAT WOULD GET THE
PUBLIC THE ANSWERS YOU JUST
DESCRIBED.
THEY WOULD HAVE A PUBLIC
HEARING.
IT ISN'T REMOVAL.
IT'S IMPEACHMENT AS AERING HA.
THEY'RE SAYING NO, NOT UNLESS
THE MUELLER REPORT COMES OUT.
>> NOT NECESSARILY.
I BELIEVE THEY ARE SETTING UP
EXPECTATIONS AND STANDARDS FOR
THE MUELLER REPORT THAT MAY WELL
BE UNJUSTIFIED, AND SORT OF
PAINTING THEMSELVES INTO A
CORNER.
BUT YOU CAN HAVE A ROBUST
INVESTIGATION WITH PUBLIC
HEARINGS INTO THE RUSSIA
CONNECTIONS AND INTO, YOU KNOW,
EMOLUMENTS, AND INTO TRUMP BAD
BUSINESS PRACTICES.
YOU CAN DO ALL THAT THROUGH
THESE COMMITTEES WITHOUT IT
BEING AN IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDING.
I WOULD ARGUE IT'S PROBABLY MORE
RESPONSIBLE OF DEMOCRATS IN
CONGRESS TO LOOK AT ALL THESE
VARIOUS THINGS THAT NEED FURTHER
DIGGING AND SCRUTINY, AND THAT
THE PUBLIC DESERVES TO KNOW
ABOUT THE SECURITY CLEARANCE
ISSUE THAT YOU TALKED ABOUT
EARLIER IN THE SHOW, AND THEY
SHOULD SPEND THEIR TIME NOT
WORRYING ABOUT TO IMPEACH OR NOT
TO IMPEACH.
GO AFTER THE TAX RETURNS, LOOK
AT THE INSURANCE ISSUES THAT
MICHAEL COHEN HAS RAISED, THE
TAX FRAUD STORY THE "NEW YORK
TIMES" PUT TOGETHER MONTHS AGO,
ABOUT THE TRUMP FAMILY GETTING
AWAY WITH HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS
OF DOLLARS IN TAX FRAUD.
THAT'S AMAZING.
THEY SHOULD LOOK AT EACH AND
EVERY ONE OF THESE AND AT THE
END OF THE DAY THEY CAN HAVE A
DEBATE OVER WHETHER TO IMPEACH
OR NOT, BY THEN IT MIGHT BE
ELECTION TIME.
THE AMERICAN PUBLIC IS OWED
ANSWERS AND YOU DON'T NEED
IMPEACHMENT TO DO THAT.
>> WE ARE OUT OF TIME, BUT CHUCK
ROSENBERG VERY QUICKLY, CAN YOU
ENVISION A LEAK OF THE MUELLER
REPORT, WHATEVER IT IS, COMING
OUT OF THAT WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL'S OFFICE IF IT'S NOT
RELEASED?
>> I CAN'T IMAGINE IT COMING
FROM THE MUELLER TEAM, JOY, BUT
ALMOST EVERYTHING BECOMES PUBLIC
IN SOME WAY AT SOME POINT.
MY GUESS IS THAT WE'LL SEE IT,
BUT WE'RE NOT GOING TO SEE IT
FROM BOB MUELLER.
HE'S RUNNING A VERY TIGHT SHIP
OVER THERE.
>> YES, HE IS.
WASHINGTON BUREAU CHIEF FOR
MOTHER JONES, CHUCK ROSENBERG
FORMER U.S. ATTORNEY FROM
VIRGINIA.
THANK YOU GUYS VERY MUCH.
>>> SO I'M NOT AN ACCOUNTANT,
TAX LAW IS NOT MY THING.
STATISTICALLY SPEAKING IT'S
PROBABLY NOT YOUR THING EITHER.
BUT THERE'S A STRONG POSSIBILITY
IT'S ABOUT TO BE.
MORE ON THAT IN A MINUTE.
STAY WITH US.
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance,
so you only pay for
what you need.
Nice. But, uh...
what's up with
your... partner?
Oh. Well, we just spend
all day telling everyone
how we customize
car insurance,
because no two people
are alike, so...
LiMu gets a
little confused
when he sees
another bird
that looks
exactly like him.
[ loud crash ]
Yeah.
He'll figure it out.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
If your moderate to
severe ulcerative colitis
or Crohn's symptoms
are holding you back,
and your current treatment
hasn't worked well enough
it may be time for a change.
Ask your doctor about ENTYVIO®,
the only biologic
developed and approved
just for UC and Crohn's.
ENTYVIO® works at the site of
inflammation in the GI tract,
and is clinically
proven to help many
patients achieve both
symptom relief and remission.
Infusion and serious allergic
reactions can happen
during or after treatment.
ENTYVIO® may
increase risk of infection,
which can be serious.
PML, a rare, serious,
potentially fatal brain
infection caused by a
virus may be possible.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection
experience frequent infections
or have flu-like
symptoms, or sores.
Liver problems can
occur with ENTYVIO®.
If your UC or Crohn's
treatment isn't working for you,
ask your gastroenterologist
about ENTYVIO®.
ENTYVIO®.
Relief and Remission
within reach.
DEALDASH.COM, THE FAIR AND
HONEST BIDDING SITE. AN IPAD WAS
SOLD FOR LESS THAN $24; A
PLAYSTATION FOR LESS THAN $16;
AND A 4K TELEVISION FOR LESS
THAN $2. GO TO DEALDASH.COM
RIGHT NOW AND SEE HOW MUCH YOU
CAN SAVE. REMEMBER, SHIPPING IS
ALWAWA
>>> THE NEW DEMOCRATIC HOUSE HAS
USHERED IN A WHOLE LOT OF
CHANGES.
APART FROM ALL THE NEW
INCREDIBLY DIVERSE FRESHMEN
MEMBERS, AND A NEW IF RETURNING
SPEAKER AT THE HELM, THE CHANGE
IN LEADERSHIP IN THE COMMITTEES
MEANS THAT WE ARE SEEING
OVERSIGHT FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE DONALD TRUMP ENTERED THE
WHITE HOUSE, AND THAT KICKED
INTO HIGH GEAR EARLIER THIS WEEK
WHEN THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN JERRY
NADLER'S COMMITTEE SENT OVER A
SWEEPING DOCUMENT REQUEST TO 81
PEOPLE AND ENTITIES RELATED TO
TRUMP WORLD.
THAT HAPPENED ON MONDAY.
ON TUESDAY WE LEARNED THAT THE
HOUSE WAYS AND MEANS COMMITTEE
IS PREPARING TO GO AFTER A
DECADE'S WORTH OF TRUMP TAX
RETURNS, AND THEY PLAN ON DOING
SO USING A 1924 LAW THAT GIVES
THE CHAIRMAN OF THAT COMMITTEE
BROAD POWER TO DEMAND THE TAX
RETURNS OF WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIALS.
IN THIS CASE THE WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIAL IS THE PRESIDENT.
TODAY WE'RE LEARNING THAT THAT
COMMITTEE MIGHT BE TAKING THAT
REQUEST ONE STEP FURTHER.
REUTERS IS REPORTING THAT
DEMOCRATS ARE LOOKING AT THE
POSSIBILITY OF BROADENING THE
REQUEST TO ASK FOR DONALD
TRUMP'S BUSINESS RETURNS.
NOW TRUMP OWNS MORE THAN 500
COMPANIES AND ENTITIES, AND WHAT
THAT EXACTLY MEANS, BASICALLY,
IS THAT DONALD TRUMP'S BUSINESS
IS NOT REALLY A BUSINESS IN THE
SENSE THAT WE UNDERSTAND IT.
THOSE MORE THAN 500 COMPANIES
ARE ALL A SERIES OF LLCs THAT
NORMALLY SHOULD SHOW UP ON YOUR
PERSONAL INCOME TAXES.
THAT SETUP IS COMMON IN THE NEW
YORK REAL ESTATE BUSINESS, SO
FOR THE COMMITTEE THE FIRST STEP
WOULD BE TO GET TRUMP'S PERSONAL
RETURNS TO LOOK FOR THOSE
500-PLUS LLC'S, AND IF THEY'RE
NOT LISTED THERE, THEN STEP TWO
WOULD BE TO TRY AND GO AND GET
DONALD TRUMP'S BUSINESS TAX
RETURNS.
IT COULD GET COMPLICATED.
THE CHAIRMAN OF THE HOUSE WAYS
AND MEANS COMMITTEE TELLS
REUTERS, QUOTE, TAX POLICY IS
PRETTY COMPLICATED.
THERE ARE TIMES WHEN INDIVIDUAL
RETURNS CAN INSTRUCT YOU.
OTHER TIMES YOU MIGHT SEEK A
BUSINESS RETURN.
THAT'S SOMETHING TO LOOK OUT
FOR, AND IT DOES MAKE YOU THINK.
IF DONALD TRUMP NEVER RAN FOR
PRESIDENT, ALL OF THIS COULD
HAVE REMAINED HIDDEN FOREVER.
SO ELECTIONS DO HAVE
CONSEQUENCES, INCLUDING FOR
DONALD TRUMP.
♪♪
♪ Do you
love me? ♪
♪ I can
really move ♪
♪ Do you love me? ♪
♪ I'm in the groove ♪
♪ now do you love me? ♪
♪ Do you love me ♪
♪ Now that I can dance? ♪
♪ Watch me now! ♪
♪ Work, work,
ah work it out baby ♪
Applebee's
3 Course Meal
starting
at $11.99.
Now that's Eatin' Good
in the Neighborhood.
TO BE NOBODY BUT YOURSELF IN A
WORLD WHICH IS DOING IT'S BEST
TO MAKE YOU EVERYBODY ELSE...
♪ ♪ ♪
MEANS TO FIGHT
THE HARDEST BATTLE,
WHICH ANY HUMAN BEING
CAN FIGHT AND NEVER STOP.
DOES THIS SOUND DISMAL?
IT ISN'T.
♪ ♪ ♪
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL LIFE ON EARTH.
♪ ♪ ♪
>>> NOW TOO MANY KIDS DON'T HAVE
PARENTS WHO CARE.
GANGS AND DRUGS HAVE TAKEN OVER
OUR STREETS AND UNDERMINED OUR
SCHOOLS.
EVERY DAY WE READ ABOUT SOMEBODY
ELSE WHO HAS LITERALLY GOTTEN
AWAY WITH MURDER.
>> AFTER LYNDON JOHNSON MADE THE
SURPRISE DECISION NOT TO RUN FOR
PRESIDENT AGAIN IN MARCH OF 1968
AND AFTER ANTI-WAR DEMOCRAT
GEORGE McGOVERN WAS BLOWN OUT OF
THE ELECTION BY LAW AND ORDER
INCUMBENT RICHARD NIXON IN 1972
DEMOCRATS WERE SHOOK.
AND AFTER THOSE PRESIDENTIAL
DEFEATS THERE WAS A WAY TO RUN
FOR PRESIDENT AS A DEMOCRAT.
THAT WAY WAS TO RUN AS A
CENTRIST, TO TRY AND RECONNECT
AS A DEMOCRAT WITH WHITE WORKING
CLASS AND WHITE SUBURBAN VOTERS
WHO FLED TO NIXON AND REAGAN IN
1980.
IT WORKED FOR BILL CLINTON, IT'S
ONE OF THE WAYS THAT CLINTON GOT
ELECTED IN 1992.
THOUGH HE WOUND UP APOLOGIZING
FOR HIS PART IN MASS
INCARCERATION ONCE HIS WIFE WAS
RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT, BEING
TOUGH ON CRIME AND FENDING OFF
REPUBLICANS ON THE ISSUE IS HOW
BILL CLINTON CAME TO SIGN THE
OMNIBUS BILL AGAINST CRIME IN
1994.
TODAY DEMOCRATS WHO ARE TRYING
TO RUN FROM THAT SAME PLAY BOOK
ARE FINDING THEMSELVES IN A VERY
DIFFERENT DEMOCRATIC PARTY WHERE
THE PROGRESSIVE WING IS GETTING
STRONGER AGAIN AND WINNING
ELECTIONS FOR CONGRESS.
CANDIDATES FOR PRESIDENT WHO
MIGHT NATURALLY HAVE APPEALED TO
THE RUST BELT WHITE WORKING
CLASS VOTER 20 YEARS AGO ARE
STRUGGLING TO FIGURE OUT A
CREDIBLE PATH TO THE NOMINATION.
THIS EARLY ON IN THE RACE.
AND IT MAY BE IMPOSSIBLE TO SAY
WHAT KIND OF CANDIDATE OR
PLATFORM WILL WORK IN THE
DEMOCRATIC PRIMARY.
JUST THIS WEEK WE'VE SEEN A
NUMBER OF POTENTIAL CANDIDATES
FROM THAT CENTRIST WING OF THE
PARTY BEG OFF FROM RUNNING,
FIRST ERIC HOLDER,
ATTORNEY
GENERAL UNDER POM IS NOT
RUNNING.
AND JEFF MERKLEY, ANOTHER CRIME
BILL YES VOTE LAST TIME, AND NEW
YORK MAYOR MICHAEL BLOOMBERG.
ALSO THIS WEEK HILLARY CLINTON
CONFIRMED IN A LOCAL TELEVISION
INTERVIEW SHE WAS NOT RUNNING
FOR PRESIDENT AGAIN, AND THE
LATEST SENATOR SHERROD BROWN
FROM OHIO ANNOUNCED HE WOULD
RATHER STAY IN THE SENATE.
WHICH BRINGS US TO JOE BIDEN,
THE FORMER VICE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES, THE RIDE OR DIE
BESTIE OF BARACK OBAMA IS
REPORTED TO BE SERIOUSLY
CONSIDERING MAKING HIS THIRD RUN
FOR PRESIDENT.
THE CHALLENGE IS JOE BIDEN COMES
FROM THAT LAW AND ORDER SCHOOL
OF DEMOCRATIC POLITICS.
WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO FIND IS THE
KIND OF DIALOGUE ON CRIME THAT
USED TO BE THE WAY THAT YOU
BECAME THE NOMINEE.
WHETHER IT'S THE WAY HE OVERSAW
THE CLEARANCE THOMAS HEARINGS
AND HIS TREATMENT OF ANITA HILL
OR THE WAY HE WROTE AND DEFENDED
THE 1994 CRIME BILL, ALL OF THAT
IS GOING TO SOUND VERY DIFFERENT
WHEN YOU HEAR IT PLAYED AGAIN
TODAY.
FOR JOE BIDEN, THE UPSIDE IS
THAT HE WOULD ENTER THE RACE AS
THE FRONT RUNNER IF HE GETS IN.
FULL STOP, HE WAS THE VICE
PRESIDENT.
EVERYBODY KNOWS HIM, BUT THE
RISK IS THE REPLAY.
TODAY "THE WASHINGTON POST"
PUBLISHED PARTS OF AN INTERVIEW
BIDEN GAVE IN 1975 TO A LOCAL
DELAWARE PAPER.
AT THE TIME HE WAS A FRESHMAN
SENATOR ON THE VERGE OF
SUCCESSFULLY PASSING A MEASURE
TO BLOCK FEDERAL FUNTDING FOR
BUSSING THAT WOULD HELP
INTEGRATE SCHOOL SYSTEMS.
HE ARGUED AGAINST THAT, SAYING,
QUOTE, THE REAL PROBLEM WITH
BUSSING.
YOU TAKE PEOPLE WHO AREN'T
RACIST, PEOPLE WHO ARE GOOD
CITIZENS WHO BELIEVE IN EQUAL
EDUCATION AND OPPORTUNITY AND
YOU STUNT THEIR CHILDREN'S
INTELLECTUAL GROWTH BY BUSSING
THEM TO AN INFERIOR SCHOOL, AND
YOU'RE GOING TO FILL THEM WITH
HATRED.
HE CONTINUED, QUOTE, I DO NOT
BUY THE CONCEPT POPULAR IN THE
'60s WHICH SAID WE HAVE
SUPPRESSED THE BLACK MAN FOR 300
YEARS AND THE WHITE MAN IS NOW
FAR AHEAD IN THE RACE FOR
EVERYTHING OUR SOCIETY OFFERS.
IN ORDER TO EVEN THE SCORE WE
MUST NOW GIVE THE BLACK MAN A
HEAD START OR EVEN HOLD THE
WHITE MAN BACK TO EVEN THE RACE.
I DON'T BUY THAT.
JOINING ME NOW IS CHIEF PUBLIC
AFFAIRS OFFICER FOR MOVEON.ORG
AND A FORMER DEPUTY DIRECTOR FOR
PRESIDENT OBAMA'S 2012 CAMPAIGN.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THIS, BIDEN'S
SPOKESMAN ON THE BUSSING ISSUE,
THIS IS A QUOTE FROM BILL RUSSO
ABOUT "THE WASHINGTON POST"
ARTICLE.
HE NEVER THOUGHT BUSSING WAS THE
BEST WAY TO INTEGRATE SCHOOLS IN
DELAWARE, A POSITION WHICH MOST
PEOPLE NOW AGREE WITH.
AND HE SAID DURING THOSE MANY
YEARS OF DEBATE THAT BUSSING
WOULD NOT ACHIEVE EQUAL
OPPORTUNITY.
SO IT LOOKS LIKE ON THIS AND ON
THE CRIME BILL AND OTHER THINGS,
TEAM BIDEN IS JUST DOUBLING DOWN
ON WHATEVER HE SAID BEFORE,
THEY'RE JUST DEFENDING IT.
IS THAT WISE IN TODAY'S VERSION
OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY?
>> NO, IT IS NOT WISE AT ALL.
AND FULL DISCLOSURE, I KNOW JOE
BIDEN WELL AS YOU MENTIONED, I
WORKED IN THE -- I WORKED FOR
OBAMA ON THE CAMPAIGN, BUT I
ALSO WORKED IN THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION WHERE I GOT TO
WORK WITH JOE BIDEN AND LOOK, IT
IS A COMPLICATED POSITION THAT
JOE BIDEN IS IN.
HE IS INCREDIBLY POPULAR.
PEOPLE REMEMBER HIM FONDLY, AND
CONNECT JOE BIDEN WITH THE
SUCCESSES OF OBAMA.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT WILL HELP HIM IN THE
PRIMARIES, ESPECIALLY IN A STATE
LIKE SOUTH CAROLINA.
WHERE JOE BIDEN IS NOW, HE'S IN
A SITUATION WHERE THE LAST TIME
THAT HE RAN ALONE WITHOUT OBAMA
WAS 12 YEARS AGO, AND NOW HE'S
GOING TO BE IN A SITUATION WHERE
HIS 40-YEAR RECORD IS GOING TO
BE EXAMINED.
THERE'S GOING TO BE A FRESH NEW
LOOK AND THINGS LIKE THE CRIME
BILL, THINGS LIKE ANITA HILL,
THE HEARING WITH THOMAS,
CLARENCE THOMAS, IS GOING TO
COME UP, AND SO THE THING HERE
IS THAT THEY HAVE TO DEAL WITH
THIS HEAD ON BECAUSE 40 YEARS
AGO, IT WAS A DIFFERENT TIME.
WE HAVE MOVED AWAY FROM THAT.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT STRUCTURAL
INEQUALITY.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THINGS THAT
HAVE REALLY HURT THE BROWN AND
BLACK COMMUNITY LIKE THE CRIME
BILL OVER THESE LAST FEW
DECADES, AND SO THEY NEED TO
TALK ABOUT HOW THAT WAS A
MISTAKE.
THEY NEED TO TALK ABOUT HOW THE
THINGS THAT HE HAS DONE IN THE
LAST 15 YEARS THAT DEALT WITH,
YOU KNOW -- THAT HE'S TALKED
ABOUT CIVIL RIGHTS ISSUES.
HE'S TALKED ABOUT WOMEN'S
ISSUES.
HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO TALK ABOUT
THAT AS WELL, BUT SAY YOU KNOW
WHAT, WHERE I WAS 40 YEARS AGO
WAS A MISTAKE AND TALK ABOUT WHY
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
BUT BY DOUBLING DOWN ON THINGS,
ON RECORDS, ON THINGS THAT HE
SAID IN 1970s ON THE CRIME BILL
WHERE HE VOTED ON ANITA HILL IS
A HUGE MISTAKE.
>> DURING THE 2016 CAMPAIGN,
YOUNG BLACK VOTERS REALLY HELD
HILLARY CLINTON, WHO WAS FIRST
LADY AT THE TIME, SHE REALLY GOT
TAGGED WITH HER COMMENT SUPER
PREDATORS ABOUT THE CRIME BILL.
IN THIS CYCLE KAMALA HARRIS IS
BEING TAGGED BY A LOT -- NOT A
LOT OF, BUT YOU KNOW, SOME
AFRICAN-AMERICAN VOTERS BECAUSE
SHE WAS A PROSECUTOR AND
PROSECUTED PEOPLE IN CALIFORNIA
AND THE WAY THAT THAT OFFICE
RAN.
CAN BIDEN -- I DON'T KNOW HOW TO
PUT THIS, BUT BIDEN'S LEGACY
RIGHT NOW IS OBAMA.
HIS SUPPORT FOR BARACK OBAMA,
HIS RIDE OR DIE SUPPORT FOR
BARACK OBAMA.
IF HE RUNS, DOES HIS LEGACY THEN
GET RELITIGATED BY YOUNG VOTERS
WHO REALLY WEREN'T AROUND DURING
HIS TENURE IN THE '90s BUT WHO
WILL NOW LEARN THE THINGS THEY
LEARNED ABOUT HILLARY CLINTON.
>> CLEARLY FOR SOME FOLKS WHO
DECIDED THEY WERE NOT GOING TO
JUMP IN, REMEMBER WE HAD THE
BLACK LIVES MATTER MOVEMENT THAT
HAPPENED AROUND THAT TIME AND
LED TO REALLY PLAYING A BIG ROLE
IN THE PRIMARY OF 2016 AS YOU
JUST MENTIONED WITH SUPER
PREDATORS THAT HILLARY CLINTON
SAID AT FIRST LADY THAT REALLY
HURT HER IN THAT PRIMARY, AND SO
WE'RE JUST IN A DIFFERENT TIME,
JOY, AND YOU CANNOT -- YOU
CANNOT GO BY AND NOT TALK ABOUT
YOUR RECORD BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING
TO BE CALLED OUT FOR IT, AND
THIS IS JUST WHERE WE ARE.
THERE IS AN ENERGY.
THERE IS AN ACTIVISM.
THERE IS A CONVERSATION
HAPPENING.
PEOPLE ARE CALLING OUT WHITE
SUPREMACY, AND WE ALSO HAVE
DONALD TRUMP WHO'S IN THE WHITE
HOUSE WHO'S DOING A BUNCH OF
THINGS THAT HURT, YOU KNOW,
FRONT LINE COMMUNITIES, SO WE
NEED CANDIDATES, NOT JUST
TALKING THE TALK, BUT WALKING
THE WALKING.
NOT JUST HAVING LINES ABOUT THE
COMMUNITY, THE AFRICAN-AMERICAN
COMMUNITY OR THE BROWN COMMUNITY
IN THEIR STUMP SPEECH, BUT
ACTUALLY PUTTING FORTH WHAT ARE
THEY GOING TO DO, AND HERE'S THE
THING, JOY, THE REALITY IS YOU
CANNOT, A DEMOCRAT CANNOT WIN
THE PRIMARY WITHOUT THE
AFRICAN-AMERICAN VOTE.
THEY CANNOT WIN THE GENERAL
ELECTION WITHOUT A HIGH TURNOUT
IN THE BLACK VOTE.
BLACK COMMUNITY AND WOMEN IN
PARTICULAR, BLACK WOMEN HOLD THE
KEY TO THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> YEAH.
AND SORT OF THE REVERSE WAY, ONE
MIGHT ENVISION SOME
FIX AN ISSUE THAT CAME UP
REGARDING PAST ASSOCIATIONS.
>> THEY HAVE TO DEAL WITH IT.
>> PEOPLE MIGHT HAVE TO DO IT.
KARINE JEAN-PIERRE FROM
MOVEON.ORG.
YOU ARE THE BEST.
>> THANKS, JOY.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
APPRECIATE YOUR TIME.
>>> UP NEXT, SPECIAL PURPOSE
COMMUNICATION TUBES.
IT'S ALL GOING TO MAKE SENSE IN
A MINUTE.
I PROMISE.
STAY WITH US.
a video of choreography.
I need my phone to work
while I'm on the subway.
You'll see me streaming a video,
trying not to fall.
(laughs)
(VO)
There when it matters.
Buy the new Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e on us.
Everyone's got to listen to mom.
When it comes to reducing the
sugar in your family's diet,
Coke, Dr Pepper and Pepsi hear
you.
We're working together to do
just that.
Bringing you more great tasting
beverages with less sugar
or no sugar at all.
Smaller portion sizes,
clear calorie labels and
reminders to think balance.
Because we know mom wants what's
best.
More beverage choices, smaller
portions, less sugar.
BalanceUS.org
There's brushing...and
there's Oral-B Power brushing.
Oral-B just cleans better.
Even my hygienist said
going electric could lead to way
cleaner teeth.
And unlike Sonicare,
Oral-B is the first electric
toothbrush brand
accepted by the ADA.
Oral-B.
Brush like a pro.
>>> SPECIAL PURPOSE
COMMUNICATION TUBES.
THEY ARE A THING THAT LOOKED
LIKE THIS.
THEY DID NOT SEEM TO DO VERY
MUCH, EVEN THOUGH THESE THREE
GENTLEMEN ARE MAKING SOME PRETTY
INTENSE EYE CONTACT WITH THEM.
THOSE TUBES HAD SOMETHING TO DO
WITH RADAR TECHNOLOGY.
THEY WERE MADE BY A COMPANY
CALLED THE INTERNATIONAL
TELEPHONE AND TELEGRAPH COMPANY,
ITT FOR SHORT.
THEY TOOK THIS VIDEO WHEN THEY
OPENED A NEW RADAR TUBE PLANT IN
VIRGINIA IN THE LATE 1950s, BUT
ITT WAS NOT JUST A SPECIAL
PURPOSE COMMUNICATION
COMMUNICATIONS TUBES COMPANY,
THEY WERE A HUGE PHONE COMPANY
IN THEIR DAY, AND IN 1970s, ITT
WANTED TO GET EVEN BIGGER.
THEY STARTED GOBBLING UP OTHER
COMPANIES TO MAKE ONE BIG
MONSTER CONGLOMERATE AND THEY
EVENTUALLY WERE SUED FOR IT FOR
ALLEGEDLY VIOLATING ANTITRUST
LAWS.
DURING THE NIXON ADMINISTRATION,
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT FILED A
LAWSUIT AGAINST ITT FOR BULKING
UP THEIR COMPANY IN A WAY THAT
POTENTIALLY VIOLATED FEDERAL
ANTITRUST LAW.
IT WAS A HUGE ORDEAL FOR ITT,
BEING SUED BY THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT, UNTIL RICHARD NIXON
MADE THE WHOLE THING GO AWAY.
IN WHAT WOUND UP BECOMING KIND
OF A SIBLING TO THE WATERGATE
INVESTIGATION, NIXON ORDERED THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT TO DROP THE
ANTITRUST LAWSUIT AGAINST ITT
AND LET THEM GO AHEAD AND MAKE
THEIR MEGA COMPANY, AND HE DID
IT IN EXCHANGE FOR A $400,000
CHECK FROM ITT WRITTEN OUT TO
THE REPUBLICAN PARTY.
THE WATERGATE SPECIAL PROSECUTOR
ARCHIBALD COX SET UP A TASK
FORCE TO INVESTIGATE THAT PAYOFF
AND THE ALLEGATION THAT THE
PRESIDENT LEANED ON THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT TO GET THEM TO DROP A
LAWSUIT.
THE SPECIAL PROSECUTOR
REPORTEDLY TURNED UP SO MUCH
EVIDENCE OF WRONGDOING AROUND
THE ITT SCANDAL THAT THEY WERE
PLANNING A PROSECUTION, BUT THEY
NEVER GOT THE CHANCE.
RICHARD NIXON, OF COURSE,
RESIGNED AND WAS PARDONED BEFORE
HE COULD BE HELD ACCOUNTABLE FOR
HIS CONDUCT IN THE OVAL OFFICE.
NOW, RACHEL HAS TALKED ABOUT
THIS ON THIS SHOW BEFORE BECAUSE
THERE IS A LESSON HERE THAT IS
IMPORTANT.
THE PRESIDENT CANNOT INTERFERE
WITH THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT.
THE PRESIDENT IS NOT ALLOWED TO
LEAN ON OR GIVE ORDERS TO THE
DOJ ABOUT WHO THEY DO AND DO NOT
PROSECUTE.
THAT KIND OF THING IS ILLEGAL.
WHETHER IT COMES WITH A $400,000
CHECK FROM THE TELEPHONE COMPANY
OR NOT.
HOLD THAT THOUGHT.
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it from
your allergy pills?
Most pills don't
finish the job
because they don't relieve
nasal congestion.
Flonase Sensimist
is different.
It relieves all
your worst symptoms,
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
It's more complete
allergy relief.
And all from a gentle mist
you can barely feel.
Flonase Sensimist helps block
six key inflammatory
substances.
Most pills only block one.
And six is
greater than one.
Flonase Sensimist.
Let's see, ALEVE is
proven better on pain
And six is
greater than one.
than Tylenol Extra Strength.
And last longer
with fewer pills.
So why am I still
thinking about this?
I'll take Aleve.
ALEVE.
Proven better on pain.
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
What do all these people
have in common, LiMu?
[ guttural grunt ]
Exactly. Nothing!
They're completely
different people.
That's why they
make customized
car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need.
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done it again, LiMu.
[ LiMu grunts ]
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
>>> THIS WEEK, JANE MAYER AT
"THE NEW YORKER" REPORTED THAT
IN 2017 THE CURRENT PRESIDENT
TRIED TO PRESSURE THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT WHEN THEY WERE TRYING
TO DECIDE WHETHER TO OPEN AN
ANTITRUST LAWSUIT AGAINST AT&T.
AT&T WAS TRYING TO MERGE WITH
TIME WARNER, WHICH OWNS, DRUM
ROLL, CNN.
THE PRESIDENT HAS REPEATEDLY
ATTACKED CNN AT HIS RALLIES AND
ON TWITTER AND MADE CNN HIS
NUMBER ONE ENEMY IN THE MEDIA.
EVEN BEFORE HE WAS ELECTED HE
SAID THAT HE DID NOT THINK THAT
THE AT&T/TIME WARNER MERGER
SHOULD GO THROUGH.
NOW, MIND YOU, BLOCKING THAT
MERGER FROM HAPPENING WOULD HAVE
BEEN REALLY BAD FOR THOSE
COMPANIES' BUSINESS, BUT DONALD
TRUMP -- FROM DONALD TRUMP'S
POINT OF VIEW, IT ALSO WOULD
HAVE BEEN A KIND OF PUNISHMENT
FOR CNN.
ACCORDING TO "THE NEW YORKER,"
DONALD TRUMP AS PRESIDENT
DEMANDED THAT HIS ADVISERS
INSTRUCT THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
TO OPEN THAT ANTITRUST
INVESTIGATION INTO AT&T.
A ROUNDABOUT WAY OF ORDERING THE
DOJ TO MEET OUT THAT PUNISHMENT
AGAINST THE COMPANY THAT OWNS
CNN BECAUSE HE DOESN'T LIKE THE
WAY HE'S BEING COVERED.
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT DID WIND
UP FILING A LAWSUIT TO BLOCK THE
AT&T MERGER THAT THE PRESIDENT
WANTED.
A CASE THAT THEY EVENTUALLY
LOST.
DOJ SAYS THE PRESIDENT HAD NO
SAY IN THEIR DELIBERATIONS WHEN
DECIDING WHETHER TO BRING THAT
SUIT, BUT NOW THAT THE DEMOCRATS
CONTROL CONGRESS, THEY SAY THEY
ARE GOING TO FIND OUT FOR SURE.
DEMOCRATS ON THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE HAVE SENT TWO LETTERS,
ONE TO THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
AND ONE TO THE WHITE HOUSE
COUNSEL, REQUESTING A TROVE OF
DOCUMENTS RELATING TO THE
PRESIDENT AND HIS INVOLVEMENT IN
THE AT&T/TIME WARNER MERGER.
THE DOCUMENT REQUEST SPANS A
TIME PERIOD OF MORE THAN TWO
YEARS.