>>> COMMENTS BY OMAR ABOUT
ISRAEL IN RECENT WEEKS HAVE BEEN
PERCEIVED AS ANTI-SEMITIC.
>> SPARKING A HOUSE RESOLUTION.
>> CONDEMNING NOT ONLY
ANTI-SEMITISM BUT ALL FORMS OF
HATE.
>> DO YOU THINK HOUSE DEMOCRATS
WATERED IT DOWN?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> I THINK IT WAS TO PROTECT --
>> THEY'RE ALL --
>> THEY HAVE BECOME THE PARTY OF
INFANTE SIDE AND SOCIALISM.
>> THERE'S ONLY SO MUCH SPEAKER
PELOSI CAN DO.
>> I THINK SHE HAS A DIFFERENT
EXPERIENCE AND USE OF WORDS
UNDERSTANDING SOME ARE FRAUGHT
WITH MEANING SHE DOESN'T
REALIZE.
>> IF YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT WORDS
MEAN CONGRESS MAY BE THE WRONG
LINE OF WORK FOR YOU.
>> COHEN SAYS IT'S MR. TRUMP
THAT'S LYING.
>> HARD TO SORTING THROUGH A HE
SAID SHE SAID ARGUMENT.
>> COHEN AND/OR HIS LAWYERS
APPROACHED THE PRESIDENT AND
ASKED FOR A PARDON.
>> WHAT THE PRESIDENT SAID --
>> OKAY.
>> THIS GUY ROUTINELY LIED.
>> ANYTHING HE SAID THAT'S NOT
DOCUMENTARY EVIDENCE, UNLESS
HE'S GETTING HIS TONGUE NOTE
RIDE.
>> IF HE'S BREATHING HE'S LIED.
>> PROBABLY MADE OVER A THOUSAND
FALSE STATEMENTS ABOUT THE
RUSSIA ISSUES.
>> DO YOU THINK THE PRESIDENT
WILL AT SOME POINT PARDON PAUL
MANAFORT?
>> I DO THINK HIS SUPPORTERS
THINK IT WILL BE EASY TO PARDON
HIM.
>> MR. MANAFORT IS A GRIFTER,
WAS WITH MR. STONE.
I'M SORRY.
HE IS A SLEAZE --
>> DEMOCRATS ARE HAVING A TOUGH
TIME TRYING TO KEEP EVERYONE IN
THEIR PARTY ON THIS SAME PAGE.
THE INFIGHTING ON HANDLING
REPRESENTATIVE ILHAN OMAR'S
COMMENTS.
SOME ON BOTH SIDES FOUND THIS TO
BE ANTI-SEMITIC WHILE
PROGRESSIVES DEFENDED IT AS
REBUKE OF ISRAEL.
A RESOLUTION THAT BROADLY
CONDEMNS HATRED.
BUT IT WAS CRITICIZED BY SOME
BEING WATERED DOWN NOT GOING FAR
ENOUGH IN REBUKING OMAR.
JUST IN TONIGHT, JONATHAN SWAN
REPORTS DURING A FRIDAY NIGHT
MAR-A-LAGO SPEECH TO DONORS, THE
PRESIDENT SAID DEMOCRATS HATE
JEWISH PEOPLE.
AND HIS SECURITY REQUIRED EVENTS
ATTENDEES TO PUT THEIR CELL
PHONES IN MAGNETIZED POUCHS
UNTIL THEY LEFT THE CLUB.
>> HOUSE SPEAKER NANCY PELOSI
TRIED TO HANDLE THE UNWIELDY
DEBATE OVER THE COMMENTS?
>> DO YOU THINK SHE UNDERSTANDS
HER COMMENTS AND WHAT HAPPENS IF
THIS HAPPENS AGAIN.
>> FIRST, THANK YOU FOR THE
QUESTION.
I DON'T THINK THAT THE
CONGRESSWOMAN PERHAPS
APPRECIATES THE FULL WEIGHT HOW
IT'S HEARD BY OTHER PEOPLE
ALTHOUGH I DON'T BELIEVE IT WAS
INTENDED IN AN ANTI-SEMITIC WAY.
>> MEANWHILE, OMAR HAS BEEN
UNWILLING TO ISSUE AND APOLOGY
ABOUT HER LATEST COMMENTS AND
DUCKED QUESTIONS ABOUT THEM.
>> Reporter: WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN
TELLING YOUR COLLEAGUES IN
PRIVATE WHO HAVE ASKED YOU ABOUT
THIS?
HAVE YOU TRIED TO EXPLAIN TO
THEM WHY IT WAS YOU SAID WHAT
YOU SAID?
HAVE YOU BEEN ABLE TO CONVINCE
THEM YOU DIDN'T INTEND FOR IT TO
BE ANTI-SEMITIC?
IS THERE A REASON YOU'RE NOT
ANSWERING QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS?
ARE YOU GOING TO APOLOGIZE?
THE CRACKS IN THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY ARE EVIDENT BOTH IN ITS
GENERATIONAL DIVIDE AND
INTENTION BETWEEN THE
ESTABLISHMENT AND MORE LEFT WING
MEMBERS, AS YOU SAW THERE.
IT'S NOT JUST ON THIS POINT.
YESTERDAY, AT THE WEST-SOUTHWEST
FESTIVAL, OCASIO-CORTEZ GAVE
THIS TAKE ON CAPITALISM.
>> CAPITALISM, TO ME, IS AN
IDEOLOGY OF CAPITAL.
IT PUTS CAPITAL, THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING IS THE
CONCENTRATION OF CAPITAL, AND IT
MEANS THAT WE SEEK AND
PRIORITIZE PROFIT AND THE
ACCUMULATION OF MONEY ABOVE ALL
ELSE AND WE SEEK IT AT ANY HUMAN
AN ENVIRONMENTAL COST.
TO ME, THAT IDEOLOGY IS NOT
SUSTAINABLE AND CANNOT BE
REDEEMED.
>> QUITE SOMETHING.
NEW POLLING BY THE DES MOINES
REGISTER CROHN INDICATES AN
APPETITE OF DEMOCRATIC VOTERS
FOR SOCIALISM WITH BERNIE
SANDERS TRAILING ONLY JOE BIDEN
AS FIRST CHOICE FOR PRESIDENT.
OF COURSE, THERE IS THE MUELLER
REPORT.
WHILE DEMOCRATS HAVE FOUGHT FOR
IT BE MADE PUBLIC, IT'S REPORTED
THE 2020 CAMPAIGN TEAMS HAVE
WRESTLED HOW TO HANDLE THE
MYRIAD SCENARIOS THEY COULD
POTENTIALLY FACE IN THE WAKE OF
ITS RELEASE AND WHAT TO DO IF IT
DOESN'T IMPLICATE THE PRESIDENT.
DEMOCRATS ALREADY FELT SOME OF
THAT BURDEN THIS WEEK WHAT THEY
SAW AS A LIGHT PRISON SENTENCE
FOR FORMER TRUMP CAMPAIGN
CHAIRMAN, PAUL MANAFORT.
THE BEAT TRUMP FERVOR AND
INVESTIGATIONS MAY BE A LOT OF
GLUE HOLDING DEMOCRATS TOGETHER
AS 2020 APPROACHES.
THE LATEST POLLING FROM IOWA
SHOW VOTERS ARE FAR LESS
CONCERNED WITH IMPEACHING
PRESIDENT TRUMP THAN THEY ARE
DEALING WITH HEALTHCARE OR
CLIMATE CHANGE.
THE CRITICAL QUESTION FOR
DEMOCRATS, CAN THEY DEFTLY
NAVIGATE THESE FRACTURES OR WILL
THEIR DIVISIONS PREVENT THEM
FROM ACHIEVING THE ONE GOAL THEY
ALL DO AGREE ON, WHICH IS
GETTING THE PRESIDENT OUT OF THE
WHITE HOUSE.
WITH ME THIS HOUR, FORMER
REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN FROM
INDIANA CLUB FOR GROWTH, DAVID
MCINTOSH.
SENIOR CORRESPONDENT FOR
WASHINGTON EXAMINER, DAVID
DRECKER AND ATKINS AND
CONTRIBUTOR MARIA KUMAR.
WE WERE HAVING A VERY SPIRITED
TOPIC ON THIS DISCUSSION ON
"MEET THE PRESS" I'D LIKE TO
PICK UP A LITTLE BIT HERE.
THERE REALLY ARE GENERATIONAL
DIFFERENCE IS AMONG DEMOCRATS, A
CERTAIN IRONY A LOT SEEM TO BE
SUPPORTING BERNIE SANDERS ONE OF
THE OLDER CANDIDATES IN THE RACE
BUT IS ON THIS FRONTIER OF
PROGRESSIVE IDEAS.
HOW DO DEMOCRATS NAVIGATE THE
IMPENDING MESS BEFORE THEM AND
THE DISAGREEMENTS OVER THIS?
>> I THINK THEY HAVE TO BE
CAREFUL THEY RECOGNIZE THE
MESSAGE THEY WILL STICK TO AND
NOT FALL INTO THE TRAP OF
BASICALLY DEFENDING EVERYTHING
THE REPUBLICANS ARE TRYING TO
STICK TO THEM.
IF YOU HEARD THIS MORNING LIZ
CHENEY WITH THE PLATFORM FOR THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY WAS GOING TO BE
AGAINST THE DEMOCRATS, SHE
TALKED ABOUT INFANTE SIDE,
IMMIGRATION, SOCIALISM AND
LASTLY SAYING DEMOCRATS ARE
ANTI-SEMITIC.
DEMOCRATS HAVE TO MAKE SURE
THEY'RE IN THEIR OWN BOXING RING
AND NOT CONSTANTLY TRYING TO
DEFEND THEMSELVES.
YOU TALK ABOUT THIS
INTERGENERATIONAL DIVIDE, IT'S
VERY REAL.
2020 IS THE FIRST TIME THERE
WILL BE MORE YOUNG VOTERS BY 12
MILLION PEOPLE THAN BABY
BOOMERS.
THEY'RE VERY UPSET.
RIGHTLY SO.
THEY ARE INHERITING AN ECONOMY
AND ENVIRONMENT THEY FEEL THEY
CANNOT ACCESS.
THE BEST WAY TO CRYSTALIZE IT IS
THE FACT YOU HAD FEDERAL
EMPLOYEES IN MIDDLE CLASS JOBS
IN BREAD LINES DURING THE FIRST
TIME.
>> DURING THE GOVERNMENT --
>> DURING THE GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN IN OVER A CENTURY.
THAT IS NOT SMALL.
>> I THINK THE ECONOMY IS THE
ISSUE.
AND ATTACKING FREE MARKETS,
YOUNG PEOPLE AND OLDER PEOPLE
KNOW A FREE ECONOMY IS A LAND OF
OPPORTUNITY.
THAT'S A VERY DANGEROUS PLACE
FOR DEMOCRATS TO LAND UP IN
THIS.
>> YOU WORK FOR CLUB FOR GROWTH
WAY ON THE OTHER SIDE OF WHAT
OCASIO-CORTEZ SAYS.
SHE IS BASICALLY THE STAR OF THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
>> MORE AMERICANS KNOW HER THAN
NANCY PELOSI OR ANY OTHER MEMBER
OF CONGRESS.
>> IT STRIKES ME THAT, YOU KNOW,
THERE IS THIS FERVOR AROUND
ISSUES LIKE MEDICARE FOR ALL,
RISING INCOME INEQUALITY.
AT WHAT POINT DOES THE VIEWPOINT
YOU ALL HAVE COME OUT OF TOUCH?
>> I THINK THE KEY FOR
REPUBLICANS AND CONSERVATIVES IS
TO SHOW HOW OUR VIEW OF FREE
MARKETS IS ACTUALLY GOOD FOR
EVERYBODY.
GOOD FOR WORKERS, MILLENNIALS,
WHETHER LOWER INCOME, HIGHER
INCOME, LAND OF OPPORTUNITY.
THAT'S THE KEY TO PORTRAY WHAT'S
GOING ON.
TAKE MEDICARE FOR ALL.
THE FLIP SIDE IS EVERY AMERICAN
IN THE COUNTRY WOULD LOSE THEIR
HEALTH INSURANCE.
MOST AMERICANS DON'T WANT TO
LOSE THEIR HEALTH INSURANCE.
>> PRIVATE HEALTH INSURANCE.
>> THEY GIVE IT UP AND SUDDENLY
THE GOVERNMENT -- AND THEY'VE
SEEN STORIES IN CANADA WHERE
PEOPLE HAVE TO WAIT FEDERAL
RESERVE TO GET CRITICAL
SURGERIES.
THEY DON'T WANT GO TO THAT.
THEY WANT TO HAVE THE BEST
HEALTHCARE IN THE WORLD AND KEEP
INSURANCE TO PAY FOR IT.
>> THEY DON'T HAVE THE BEST
HEALTHCARE IN THE WORLD, MANY
DON'T HAVE ANY HEALTHCARE.
>> NO, EVERYBODY HAS HEALTHCARE.
YOU KNOW THAT'S NOT TRUE.
ANYBODY CAN GO TO A HOSPITAL OR
URGENT CARE WHETHER THEY CAN PAY
OR NOT AND GET GOOD HEALTHCARE.
[TALKING OVER EACH OTHER ].
>> BEFORE OBAMACARE, THE NUMBER
ONE REASON FAMILIES DECLARED
BANKRUPTCY WAS BECAUSE OF
MEDICAL BILLS.
AFTER OBAMACARE -- NOT THAT IT'S
PERFECT BUT GETS PEOPLE CLOSER
TO GROUP.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT A GROUP OF
INDIVIDUALS THAT DON'T HAVE
ACCESS TO THE ECONOMY.
THEY DON'T WANT TO BUY A CAR,
CAN'T AFFORD A HOUSE.
THEY ARE WELCOMING THIS IDEA OF
A MORE COLLECTIVE ECONOMY.
>> I THINK THIS IS THE ARGUMENT
WE WILL SEE IN 2020 FOR THE MOST
PART.
THE CANDIDATE THAT GETS IT RIGHT
LEAVES IDEOLOGY BEHIND IN A WAY
AND TRIES TO TALK TO VOTERS
WHERE THEY ARE ABOUT THE
PROBLEMS THAT ARE FACING THEM.
MOST VOTERS ARE A LOT LESS
IDEOLOGY THAN WE ARE.
THEY LOOK AT THE WORLD WITHOUT A
PHILOSOPHICAL LENS, HAVING
PROBLEMS AND WHEN SOMEONE SHOWS
UP SAYING I CAN FIX THINGS AND
THEY LOOK AT IT AND SAY, I GUESS
I'M THAT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
DEMOCRATS CANNOT BE DEFENSIVE,
AT THE SAME TIME, THEY CAN'T BE
DEFENSIVE.
IF JOHN HICKENLOOPER, SOMEBODY
SAY, ARE YOU CAPITALIST?
ARE YOU A DEMOCRAT?
PROUD COLORADO AN?
LABEL, I DON'T LIKE THAT.
FOR A LOT OF YOUNGER VOTERS THAT
HAVE LIVED IN A POST COLD WAR
WORLD THEY DON'T THINK SOCIALISM
IS VENEZUELA.
>> IT'S SWEDEN?
>> IT'S LIKE THE UNITED STATES
JUST LIKE IT IS ONLY I GET MORE
STUFF.
>> THAT ISN'T THE CASE.
>> IF THEY THINK THAT YOU HAVE
TO BE WILLING TO SPEAK TO THAT
AND NOT DISMISS IT.
THIS IS 1984 ANYMORE, 2020.
>> THEY DON'T THINK SOCIALISM --
THEY THINK IT'S SOMETHING
DIFFERENT.
I WANT TO SEE THE POLL NUMBER
FOR PEOPLE IN THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY WHO LIKE THE FACT WE'RE
TALKING MEDICARE FOR ALL AND
GREEN NEW DEAL KNOWING THAT
PROBABLY WON'T HAPPEN AND
ACTUALLY KNOW HOW MANY TIMES THE
WORLD SOCIALISM IS SAID, AMERICA
WILL NOT TURN TO A SOCIALIST
COUNTRY AND THAT'S WHERE THE
ENERGY OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY
IS.
>> SHE'S RIGHT ABOUT THE
AMBITION.
YOU LOOK HOW TRUMP AND SANDERS
WERE SUCCESSFUL IN 2016, THEY
SAID ALL SORTS OF THINGS THEY
KNEW WOULDN'T HAPPEN.
IN FOR STANCE, I WILL BUILD THE
WALL AND MEXICO WILL PAY FOR IT.
THE VOTERS APPRECIATED THE
AMBITION.
YOU HAVE TO BE AMBITIOUS, I
CAN'T DO THAT BECAUSE I CAN'T
PAY FOR IT.
IF ANYTHING, HILLARY CLINTON WAS
PUNISHED FOR TELLING VOTERS,
SORRY, I CAN'T DO THAT FOR YOU,
THAT'S OUT THERE ON A LIMB.
TO YOUR POINT, I WONDER IF
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR PEOPLE TO
TALK ABOUT THINGS ASPIRATIONAL
BUT THEY CAN'T --
>> THAT'S DRIVING THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY RIGHT NOW.
THEY NEED THAT ENERGY.
THE DEMOCRATIC BASE IS SO
DIVERSE, CULTURALLY DIVERSE,
RACIALLY DIVERSE AND
ECONOMICALLY DIVERSE IN A WAY
THE REPUBLICANS HAVE NOT.
THE REPUBLICANS HAVE UNIFIED
BEHIND DONALD TRUMP AND THEY
NEED THAT ENERGY LEADING INTO
2020.
>> SOMETHING WE CAN'T FORGET 100
YEARS AGO WAS THE NEW DEAL, NOT
THE BABY BOOMERS BUT THE PARENTS
WHO SAID WE WILL MAKE A BIG BET
OR AMERICA AND INVEST BECAUSE
WE'RE GETTING OUT OF WAR AND
DEPRESSION BECAUSE WE HAVE
COMPLETE CHAOS.
HOW DO WE INVEST IN AMERICA.
BABY BOOMERS SPENT EVERYTHING
FOR THEMSELVES AND SPENT THEIR
FUTURE.
YOU HAVE 100 YEARS LATER THESE
MILLENNIALS SAYING, YOU KNOW
WHAT, WE KIND OF WANT TO GO BACK
TO WHAT YOUR GREAT-GRANDPARENTS
WANTED, BECAUSE THAT DOESN'T
SOUND SO BAD.
>> BERNIE SANDERS AND DONALD
TRUMP ON ONE SIDE AND THE REST
ON THE OTHERS, PRO WASHINGTON OR
ANTI-WASHINGTON.
TRUMP HAS STILL MAINTAINED THAT
ANTI-WASHINGTON VOICE.
IT WILL BE INTERESTING TO SEE ON
THE DEMOCRATIC SIDE WHO EMERGES
AS THE BEST CONTENDER TO DO
THAT.
>> DAVID HAS A REALLY GOOD POINT
THERE.
THAT IS PROBABLY DEFINING OUR
POLITICS MORE THAN LEFT-RIGHT,
PRO WASHINGTON, ANTI-WASHINGTON.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>>> BEFORE THE BREAK, I WANT TO
SHOW YOU WHAT JEANINE PIERO SAID
ABOUT OMAR.
SHE BASICALLY SAID OUT LOUD WHAT
MANY HAVE BEEN TALKING ABOUT
BEHIND THE SCENES WHY IT WAS SHE
MAY HAVE GOTTEN SO MUCH
CRITICISM.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> THIS IS NOT WHO YOUR PARTY
IS.
YOUR PARTY IS NOT ANTI-ISRAEL,
SHE IS.
THINK ABOUT THIS.
SHE'S NOT GETTING THIS
ANTI-ISRAEL SENTIMENT DOCTRINE
FROM THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
SO IF IT'S NOT ROOTED IN THE
PARTY, WHERE IS SHE GETTING IT
FROM?
THINK ABOUT IT.
OMAR WEARS A HIJAB, WHICH
ACCORDING TO THE KORAN, 33:59,
TELLS WOMEN TO COVER SO THEY
WON'T GET MOLESTED.
IS HER ADHERENCE TO THIS ISLAMIC
DOCTRINE INDICATIVE OF HER
ADHERENCE TO SHARIA LAW WHICH IN
ITSELF IS ANTI-THETICAL TO THE
CONSTITUTION?
>> I WOULD LIKE TO POINT OUT THE
UNITED STATES PROTECTS FREEDOM
OF RELIGION.
WHEN YOU WATCH THAT CLIP,
CLEARLY THE REMARKS SHE HAS MADE
ABOUT ISRAEL HAVE VERY MUCH
OFFENDED MANY JEWISH MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS AND HAVE BEEN CALLED
REPEATEDLY ANTI-SEMITIC.
HOW MUCH PRESSURE IS COMING ONTO
HER BECAUSE SHE IS THE FIRST
PERSON TO WEAR A HIJAB.
>> I THINK SADLY -- FIRST OF
ALL, IT'S NOT JUST FOLKS OF THE
JEWISH FAITH, FOLKS ALLIES WHO
SAID WHAT SHE SAID WAS WRONG.
>> WAS NOT OKAY.
>> WHAT WE NEED TO MAKE SURE WHO
IS BASICALLY PEDALLING
ANTI-SEMITISM AND NOT HAVING A
CONVERSATION WHERE WE SHOULD NOT
ALLOW IT AND HAVE ZERO TOLERANCE
IS COMPLETELY INAPPROPRIATE.
SHE WAS IN THE SHADOWS BUT
TRYING TO HINT AT THE FACT
BECAUSE SHE WEARS A HIJAB AND
BECAUSE OF HER MUSLIM FAITH SHE
CANNOT BE AMERICAN AND THAT IS
SOMETHING WE SHOULD ALL STAND UP
AGAINST.
>> AND LOOK, CONGRESSWOMAN OMAR
HAD DEATH THREATS AND THINGS
POSTED ABOUT HER ON SOCIAL MEDIA
IS ABHORRENT AND THIS KIND OF
TALK FEEDS DIRECTLY INTO THAT
SHE IS A MUSLIM AMERICAN,
ANTI-SEMITIC, ANTI-AMERICAN,
THAT SHOULD BE CONDEMNED, TOO.
IT'S TOUGH.
I THINK DEMOCRATS ARE FINDING A
TOUGH TIME PUSHING BACK AGAINST
THIS IDEA WHERE THE LINE IS
DRAWN ABOUT HAVING A FRANK
DISCUSSION ABOUT U.S.-ISRAELI
POLICY AND WHERE THAT CROSSES
OVER THE LINE AND REPUBLICANS
ARE COMING IN THAT SPACE AND
PUSHING, BULLDOZING OVER THE
LABELING, DEMOCRATS AS
ANTI-JEWISH AND ANTI-ISRAELI
PARTY.
I SPOKE TO FOLKS CLOSE TO THE
BENJAMIN NETANYAHU DURING THE
OBAMA ADMINISTRATION.
ED A CRITICAL AS THEY WERE AND
THEY WERE CRITICAL AND PULLED NO
PUNCH, NOBODY ACCUSED THEM OF
BEING ANTI-JEWISH OR
ANTI-ISRAEL, THEY WERE STAUNCHLY
OPPOSED TO HIM ON POLICY BUT
THAT NUANCE SEEMS TO BE LOST ON
THE REPUBLICANS MESSAGING RIGHT
NOW.
>> WE HAVE SO MUCH TO COME.
CONGRESSWOMAN MAZIE HIRONO JOINS
ME AND TO PUT MORE JUDGES ON
FEDERAL BENCHES.
MSNBC EXPLORES WHAT WE KNOW
ABOUT THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND VLADIMIR
PUTIN.
WATCH "RUSSIA IF YOU'RE
LISTENING," WITH ALI VELSCHI.
HI
Good, cuz I'm a little
worried about
my information getting out.
Why's that?
[bird speaking]
My social is 8- 7- 5 dash
Okay, I see.
[bird laughing]
SOMEBODY thinks it's hilarious.
Free Social Security
Alerts from Discover.
SOMEBODY thinks it's hilarious.
More than half of our
community
have discovered
their Irish roots.
Which means your smiling eyes,
might be Irish too.
Order AncestryDNA,
And find the surprises
in you.
Just $59 through March 18th.
Get your kit today.
If your moderate to
severe ulcerative colitis
or Crohn's symptoms
are holding you back,
and your current treatment
hasn't worked well enough
it may be time for a change.
Ask your doctor about ENTYVIO®,
the only biologic
developed and approved
just for UC and Crohn's.
ENTYVIO® works at the site of
inflammation in the GI tract,
and is clinically
proven to help many
patients achieve both
symptom relief and remission.
Infusion and serious allergic
reactions can happen
during or after treatment.
ENTYVIO® may
increase risk of infection,
which can be serious.
PML, a rare, serious,
potentially fatal brain
infection caused by a
virus may be possible.
Tell your doctor if you
have an infection
experience frequent infections
or have flu-like
symptoms, or sores.
Liver problems can
occur with ENTYVIO®.
If your UC or Crohn's
treatment isn't working for you,
ask your gastroenterologist
about ENTYVIO®.
ENTYVIO®.
Relief and Remission
within reach.
Ends March 17th.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO KASEY D.C.
JOINING US IS CONGRESSWOMAN
MAZIE HIRONO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> IN THE HOUSE, THEY HAVE SOME
MORE TOOLS AT THEIR DISPOSAL.
WHAT IS YOUR ASSESSMENT SO FAR
HOW DEMOCRATS ARE HANDLING THE
CAREFUL BALANCE MAKING SURE
THEY'RE INVESTIGATING THE
PRESIDENT WITHOUT GOING TOO FAR
AND TURNING IT INTO A POLITICAL
CIRCUS SOME SOURCES HAVE SAID TO
ME IS A CONCERN OF THEIRS.
DO YOU THINK THEY'RE STRIKING
THE RIGHT BALANCE?
>> I THINK SO BECAUSE THERE IS
SO MUCH GOING ON THAT NEEDS TO
BE INVESTIGATED BY THE TRUMP
ORGANIZATION.
THERE ARE COMMITTEES LOOKING
INTO FIVE ASPECTS OF THE
FOUNDATION INCLUDING HIS TAX
RETURNS AND IT DID NOT HAPPEN IN
THE LAST TWO YEARS WITH CONTROL
OF THE HOUSE AND CONTRAST TO 85
PEOPLE AND IN WHITEWATER WHERE A
THOUSAND REQUESTS CAME OUT AND
WHAT CAME OUT OF THAT?
NOTHING.
THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT BECAUSE
THERE ARE SO MANY ALLEGATIONS
ABOUT TRUMP, CAMPAIGN FINANCE
VIOLATIONS, ALL KINDS OF THINGS.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE NEED TO KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH THIS
PRESIDENT AND HIS ORGANIZATION.
>> ONE SOURCE OF MINE DESCRIBED
WHAT'S GOING ON IN THE HOUSE AS
AN INSURANCE POLICY FOR
POTENTIAL IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDINGS DOWN THE LINE IF THE
MUELLER REPORT DOESN'T PRODUCE A
SMOKING GUN.
DO YOU VIEW IT THAT WAY?
>> I THINK THERE ARE LEGITIMATE
AREAS OF INVESTIGATION THE HOUSE
HAS TO PURSUE.
THE MORE INVESTIGATION, REALLY,
HE WAS FOCUSED ON THE RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE WITH OUR ELECTIONS
AND ANY COOPERATION,
COLLABORATION BY THE TRUMP
ORGANIZATION, THAT IS A
RELATIVELY LIMITED SCOPE,
ALTHOUGH OUT OF THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION THERE ARE OTHER
INVESTIGATIONS BEING CONDUCTED
IN U.S. ATTORNEY'S OFFICES IN
WASHINGTON, D.C. AND IN NEW
YORK.
THERE ARE SO MANY AREAS OF
INQUIRY.
THEREFORE, WE'RE NOT LOOKING AT
THE MUELLER INVESTIGATION AS BE
ALL AND END ALL.
THERE WILL BE OTHER
INVESTIGATIONS THAT MUST
CONTINUE.
>> I'M INTERESTED TO HEAR YOU
SAY THAT.
I HAVE ASKED THIS QUESTION OF
MANY PEOPLE ABOUT IMPEACHMENT SO
FAR.
THE ANSWER IS ALWAYS WE NEED TO
ALLOW MUELLER TO FINISH HIS
WORK.
WOULD YOU SAY IF MUELLER
FINISHES, THERE IS NO SMOKING
GUN, WOULD YOU BE READY TO SAY
THE INFORMATION YOU HAVE SO FAR
IS ENOUGH TO IMPEACH THIS
PRESIDENT.
NO.
BECAUSE AS I SAID, THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION WAS VERY FOCUSED
ON RUSSIA AND ANY TRUMP
COLLABORATION, COLLUSION, SETRA
SETRA
-- ET CETERA VERY LIT TO DO
WITH CAMPAIGN SPENDING
VIOLATION, HIS FOUNDATION, MONEY
RAISED FOR HIS INAUGURATION.
THERE ARE SO MANY OTHER AREAS OF
INQUIRY INCLUDING BY THE WAY, I
WOULD SAY DONALD TRUMP IS
VIOLATING THE CONSTITUTION ON
IMMOLLMENTS CLAUSE.
THERE ARE A LOT OF AREAS.
IT IS VERY IMPORTANT THE MUELLER
INVESTIGATION FOR THE LONGEST
TIME WE WERE VERY CONCERNED
WOULD BE STOPPED IN SOME WAY.
I AM HOPING THAT BY NOW IT HAS
GONE FAR ENOUGH THERE WILL BE
COMPLETION.
AT THE SAME TIME, I WANT TO MAKE
SURE OUR NEW ATTORNEY GENERAL
RELEASES THE REPORT OF THE
INVESTIGATION TO MAKE IT AS
TRANSPARENT AS POSSIBLE AND HE
CERTAINLY DIDN'T AGREE THAT WAS
WHAT WAS GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> I WANT TO ASK YOU ALSO ABOUT
THE FEDERAL JUDICIARY, AT THE
RATE AT WHICH MITCH McCONNELL
HAS BEEN PUSHING JUDGES THROUGH
THE SENATE, PRESIDENT TRUMP
COULD HAVE PUT AS MUCH AS 20% OF
SERVING FEDERAL JUDGES ON LOWER
COURTS ON THE BENCH AND TALKING
POTENTIALLY ABOUT USING THE
QUOTE UNQUOTE NUCLEAR OPTION TO
CHANGE THE SENATE RULES TO ALLOW
THESE JUDGES TO BE CONFIRMED
MORE QUICKLY.
HOW MUCH IN YOUR VIEW IS THIS
DAMAGING THE COUNTRY AND WHAT'S
YOUR RESPONSE TO McCONNELL'S
POSSIBLE IDEA HERE?
>> MITCH McCONNELL HAS ALREADY
USED THE NUCLEAR OPTION WITH
REGARD TO THE SUPREME COURT
JUSTICES.
THERE'S MANY ORDERS OF MAGNITUDE
OF HARM THAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT NINE JUSTICES ON
THE SUPREME COURT VERSUS THE
HUNDREDS OF JUDGES THAT THERE
ARE ON CIRCUIT AND DISTRICT
COURTS.
THERE'S SOME 850 JUDGES.
HE ALREADY EXERCISED THE NUCLEAR
OPTION, WHY HE WAS ABLE TO GET
TWO PEOPLE, VERY CONSERVATIVE
IDEOLOGICALLY DRIVEN JUDGES,
ESPECIALLY CAVANAUGH, ONTO THE
SUPREME COURT.
COURTPACING IS GOING ON A PACE
WITH THESE RIGHT WING
IDEOLOGICAL JUDGES, SOME 80% OF
CIRCUIT JUDGES ARE MEMBERS OF
THE FEDERAL LIST SOCIETY, TRUMP
NOMINEES.
ALMOST 10% OF THE JUDICIARY WILL
BE TRUMP JUDGES.
WHAT DOES THAT DO TO THE
INDEPENDENCE OF THE JUDICIARY.
I HAVE MAJOR CONCERNS ABOUT
THAT.
IT WILL BE, IN MY VIEW,
DAMAGING.
IT WILL BE TRUMP'S LEGACY AMONG
THE MOST DAMAGING STARTING WITH
THE TWO ON THE UNITED STATES
SUPREME COURT.
YOU WILL SEE A LOT MORE 5-4
SPLIT DECISIONS BECAUSE OF THE
JUSTICES.
THAT IS NOT GOOD FOR THE SUPREME
COURT.
WANT THE SUPREME COURT TO HAVE
AS MUCH UNANIMITY AS POSSIBLE TO
RELATE TO ALL THE CIRCUIT COURTS
WHAT THE STATE OF THE LAW IS.
THAT IS NOT WHAT IS PLANNED.
>> BEFORE I LET YOU GO, I WANT
TO TALK ABOUT THE DEMOCRATIC
PARTY, EMERGING PRIMARY BUT ALSO
SOME DIVISIONS THAT HAVE
UNFOLDED OVER THE PAST WEEK OR
SO.
ILHAN OMAR WAS TALKING AT A
FUND-RAISING EVENT AND TALKED
ABOUT LOYALTY TO A FOREIGN
COUNTRY, AND THOSE COMMENTS WERE
CONDEMNED BY MANY DEMOCRATS AS
ANTI-SEMITIC.
DO YOU BELIEVE HER COMMENTS WERE
ANTI-SEMITIC?
>> I DON'T THINK SHE INTENDED
HER COMMENTS TO BE ANTI-SEMITIC.
WE'RE IN AN ENVIRONMENT NOW
WHERE JUST ABOUT EVERYTHING WE
SAY CAN BE VIEWED IN A CERTAIN
WAY.
WHAT WE HAVE IS A LOT OF HATE
SPEECH AGAINST IMMIGRANTS,
AGAINST MUSLIMS, ALL KINDS OF
PEOPLE.
THAT IS WHY I'M GLAD THAT WHEN
THE HOUSE ACTUALLY TOOK A VOTE
THAT THEY BASICALLY CONDEMNED
ALL HATE SPEECH.
WE CERTAINLY ARE HEARING A LOT
OF HATE SPEECH FROM THE
REPUBLICANS AND THE RIGHT.
FOR THEM TO SUDDENLY REAR UP ON
THEIR HIND LEGS AND GO AFTER ONE
PERSON, I THINK WE SHOULD BE
LOOKING AT OURSELVES AND SAYING
WE HAVE AN ENVIRONMENT NOW WHERE
BASICALLY PRESIDENT TRUMP IN HIS
CAMPAIGN REALLY EXPOSED A LOT OF
THE DIVISIVENESS AND ISSUES IN
OUR COUNTRY THAT WE'VE NEVER
FACED UP TO INCLUDING RACISM,
INCLUDING ANTI-IMMIGRANT AND
ANTI-LGBTQ AND THESE ARE ALL
AREAS WE NEED TO FACE AS A
COUNTRY.
>> FINALLY, ON 2020, MANY OF
YOUR COLLEAGUES IN THE SENATE
ARE RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT.
HAVE YOU AT THIS POINT DECIDED
YOU ARE READY TO SUPPORT ONE OF
THESE DEMOCRATS IN THE PRIMARY
IN 2020?
>> I'M JUST GLAD ON OUR SIDE WE
HAVE AN ABUNDANCE OF RICHES WITH
ALL THESE PEOPLE RUNNING.
WE SHARE VERY COMMON IDEAS.
WE BELIEVE IN THE SCIENCE, OF
COURSE.
IT'S NOT A BELIEF OR RELIGION.
SCIENCE BEHIND CLIMATE CHANGE
AND THE FACT WE HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
WE BELIEVE HEALTHCARE IS A
RIGHT, NOT A PRIVILEGE.
I THINK MOST OF THE CANDIDATES
ASCRIBE TO THAT.
>> ANYBODY STAND OUT TO YOU?
>> I THINK PRETTY MUCH ALL OF
THEM ARE REALLY GOOD ON A LOT OF
BASIC ISSUES.
ECONOMIC EQUALITY, SOCIAL
JUSTICE, ECONOMIC EQUALITY.
I DON'T HEAR THE OTHER SIDE
TALKING ABOUT THOSE ISSUES.
>> SENATOR MAZIE HIRONO, THANK
YOU FOR COMING ON THE PROGRAM.
SEE YOU ON THE HILL COMING UP
THIS WEEK.
STILL TO COME, THE PRESIDENT HAS
EXPECTED TO REVEAL HIS BUDGET
TOMORROW.
IT WON'T BALANCE FOR MORE THAN A
DECADE.
WE WILL TALK ABOUT HOW DEFIANT
CONSERVATIVES HAVE STARTED TO
SING FROM THE SAME HYMNAL AS THE
PRESIDENT EVEN THOUGH IT DOESN'T
ALIGN WITH THEIR PHILOSOPHY.
BACK AFTER THIS.
ce. But, uh...
what's up with
your... partner?
Oh. Well, we just spend
all day telling everyone
how we customize
car insurance,
because no two people
are alike, so...
LiMu gets a
little confused
when he sees
another bird
that looks
exactly like him.
[ loud crash ]
Yeah.
He'll figure it out.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS SET TO
RELEASE HIS 2020 BUDGET PROPOSAL
TOMORROW SETTING THE STAGE FOR
YET ANOTHER FIGHT WITH
DEMOCRATS.
THE PRESIDENT IS SEEKING 8.6
BILLION DOLLARS TO BUILD MORE
SECTIONS ON THE SOUTHERN BORDER
AND MAJOR BUDGET CUTS TO A RANGE
OF PROGRAMS.
>> THE PRESIDENT IS PROPOSING
ROUGHLY A 5% ACROSS THE BOARD ON
SPENDING DOMESTIC ACCOUNTS.
>> IT WILL BE ANOTHER FIGHT
ABOUT THE WALL?
>> I GUESS THERE IS.
THE BORDER WALL FOR SECURITY IS
VERY IMPORTANT, WE HAVE A CRISIS
DOWN THERE AND THE PRESIDENT HAS
MADE THAT CASE VERY EFFECTIVELY.
>> DEMOCRATS HAVE BEEN DOWN THIS
ROAD BEFORE AND ALREADY GEARING
UP FOR A FIGHT.
THE PANEL IS ALREADY BACK WITH
ME.
DAVID, I HATE TO BE A DOWNER BUT
DOES THE BUDGET MATTER.
>> IT DOES FROM A POLICY
PERSPECTIVE.
THIS IS HOW THE PRESIDENT
SIGNALS ITS PRIORITIES OF IT.
THE DEBT AND DEFICITS, VOTERS
DON'T CARE ABOUT IT.
THERE IS NO CONSTITUENCY.
>> THEY USED TO.
>> THERE IS NO CONSTITUENCY FOR
KEEPING IT IN CONTROL, IT IS THE
CONSTITUENCY THAT DOESN'T HAVE
THE POWER TO SPEND ANY MONEY.
IF YOU'RE A REPUBLICAN VOTER YOU
PROBABLY SUPPORT ALL THE THINGS
PRESIDENT TRUMP WANTS TO SPEND
ON.
IF YOU'RE A DEMOCRATIC VOTER,
YOU PROBABLY DON'T LIKE IT.
WHEN THE TABLES ARE TURNED,
REPUBLICANS WILL WANT TO HOLD
DOWN SPENDING AND DEMOCRATS WANT
TO SPEND LIKE CRAZY.
THAT IS WHY YOU KEEP GETTING
WEATHER THAT DON'T ADDRESS ANY
OF THIS.
NOTHING WILL CHANGE UNTIL VOTERS
CHANGE THEIR MINDS.
WHY DO THESE GUYS ACT LIKE THEY
DON'T WANT TO GET REELECTED.
THEY WILL WHEN THEY THINK
SOMEBODY CARES ABOUT KNIT.
>> BUDGETS NEVER MATTER.
THEY SET OUT THE PRIORITY OF THE
PRESIDENT.
THEY NEVER PASS CONGRESS IN ITS
FORM.
THIS IS A WALL, A DOCUMENT THAT
ALLOWS HIM TO PUSH FORWARD
SAYING HE'S FIGHTING FOR THE
WALL.
THE DEMOCRATS WON'T GIVE HIM THE
MONEY.
THAT BOLSTERS HIS 2020 NARRATIVE
WHAT HE'S USING THIS FOR.
>> LET'S LISTEN ONE YEAR AGO ON
THE DEFICIT.
>> WE HAVE A TRADE DEFICIT WITH
ALL COUNTRY IN THE WORLD.
LISTEN TO THIS NUMBER.
IF THERE'S ANY CHILDREN IN THE
ROOM, PLEASE CLOSE YOUR EARS.
WE HAVE A TRADE DEFICIT OF
ALMOST $800 BILLION A YEAR.
WHO MAKES THESE DEALS?
WITH MEXICO -- HE SAYS, OBAMA.
HONESTLY, IN ALL FAIRNESS TO
OBAMA, IT'S MORE THAN OBAMA,
IT'S PLENTY OF PEOPLE, BELIEVE
ME.
PLENTY OF PRESIDENTS ALLOWED
THAT TO HAPPEN AND PEOPLE THAT
WORK FOR THE PRESIDENT.
>> DAVID MCINTOSH, YOU MADE A
CAREER UNDERSTANDING ECONOMIC
POLICY.
DOES THE PRESIDENT UNDERSTAND
ECONOMIC POLICY?
>> LET ME SAY THIS.
>> IT'S A YES OR NO QUESTION.
>> I THINK HE DOES.
HE HAS AN INTUITIVE SENSE ABOUT
IT.
>> ECONOMICS IS NOT INTUITIVE,
QUANTITATIVE.
THE TRADE DEFICIT IS NOT A BIG
PROBLEM FOR THE UNITED STATES.
THE BIGGER PROBLEM DAVID DRUKKER
POINTED OUT, WASHINGTON HAS
LULLED THE PUBLIC TO THINK IT'S
OKAY FOR US TO KEEP BORROWING
AND MORTGAGING OUR FUTURE.
THAT'S WHAT THE CLUB FOR GROWTH
REALLY DOESN'T LIKE ABOUT THIS
BUDGET.
A MOVE IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
A 5% CUT IS VERY GOOD.
MILLENNIALS, IF ANYBODY, SHOULD
BE VERY WORRIED ABOUT THIS
CONTINUED DEBT AND DEFICIT
SPENDING BECAUSE THEY'RE THE
ONES THAT ULTIMATELY WILL HAVE
TO PAY FOR IT.
>> WHAT I FIND AMUSING THAT WAS
A YEAR AGO TO BRING THE TRADE
DEFICIT DOWN.
THIS IS THE OPPOSITE PRESIDENT
BECAUSE UNDER HIS WATCH HE
EXACERBATED THE TRADE DEFICIT.
THE FACT HE GAVE MONEY BACK TO
AMERICANS, WHAT DID THEY DO?
BY TRADED GOODS.
>> BECAUSE THEY'RE CHEAP.
>> YES.
BECAUSE THEY'RE CHEAP.
AND DOES HE UNDERSTAND ECONOMIC
PRINCIPLES?
THAT SOUND BITE INDICATES HE
DOES NOT.
>> LET ME DEFEND THE PRESIDENT A
LITTLE BIT.
HE UNDERSTAND THE TAX CUT WOULD
GROW THE ECONOMY.
A BENEFIT OF THAT IS THAT
AMERICANS GET MORE MONEY IN
THEIR POCKET TO SPEND AND THEY
SPEND ON GOOD DEALS.
THAT MEANS IMPORTED GOODS.
I THINK THE PRESIDENT DOES
UNDERSTAND ECONOMICS IN
FOCUSSING ON GROWTH.
THE TRADE DEFICIT IS NOT THE BIG
PROBLEM.
THERE ARE SOME PROBLEMS.
HE NEEDS A GOOD DEAL WITH CHINA
TO FORCE THEM TO RESPECT OUR
PROPERTY RIGHTS.
THAT'S A GOOD ISSUE TO DEAL
WITH.
THE AMOUNT OF THE TRADE DEFICIT
HAS MORE WITH THE ECONOMIES OF
THE WORLD NOT DOING SO WELL.
NA THE PRESIDENT ALSO THINKS
TARIFFS THAT ENRICH THE TREASURY
ARE COMING FROM FOREIGN
COUNTRIES, OF COURSE, THEY'RE
COMING FROM US JUST LIKE A TAX.
I THINK DAVID'S RIGHT IN THAT
THE PRESIDENT HAS A GENERAL
MACRO CONSERVATIVE APPROACH THE
ECONOMY, IF I PUT MORE MONEY
BACK INTO THE HANDS OF
BUSINESSES AND PEOPLE --
>> HAVING BEEN A BUSINESSMAN.
>> THEY'LL SPEND MONEY.
THE PRESIDENT, IRONICALLY HERE,
ALSO BELIEVES, IN A SENSE THE
WAY YOU REALLY MAKE THIS WORK IS
BE A CRONY CAPITALIST.
IN OTHER WORDS, I WILL USE THE
HEAVY HAND OF THE GOVERNMENT AND
MY INFLUENCE TO CALL
CORPORATIONS, STOP THEM FROM
MOVING OVERSEAS.
IF THEY THINK THEY CAN PRODUCE A
BETTER CHEAPER PRODUCT TO KEEP
THEIR BUSINESS AFLOAT, I WILL
REGULATE MARKETS IN A MORE
TIGHTLY REGULATED WAY THROUGH
TRADE DEALS RATHER THAN GENERAL
FREE MARKET APPROACH THAT ALLOW
COUNTRIES TO INTERACT WITH EACH
OTHER.
>> IT'S VERY CONTRARY TO
TRADITIONAL REPUBLICAN DOCTRINE
IN MANY WAYS.
THIS IS YET ANOTHER SPIRITED
DISCUSSION I HAVE TO PUT ON
PAUSE.
>>> COMING UP, ONE HAS A
POLITICAL RECORD MORE THAN FOUR
DECADES LONG AND THE OTHER 46
YEARS OLD.
HOW JOE BIDEN AND BETO O'ROURKE
COULD UP-END THE 2020 RACE AND
WHY THEY HAVEN'T JUMPED IN YET.
>>> MY ILLUSTRIOUS PRODUCERS
FOUND A SIMPSON PIECE JUST FOR
YOU FROM 20 YEARS AGO.
>> AS YOU UNDERSTAND WE
INHERITED A BUDGET CRUNCH FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HOW BAD IS IT?
>> WE'RE BROKE.
>> THE COUNTRY IS BROKE?
HOW CAN THAT BE?
♪ A sock-a-bam-boom ♪
♪ Who's in the room? ♪
♪ Love is dangerous ♪
♪ But driving safe
means you pay less ♪
♪ Switch and save ♪
♪ Yes, ma'am ♪
Excuse me, miss.
♪ Does this heart
belong to you? ♪
♪ Would you like it anyway? ♪
[ Scatting ]
TO BE NOBODY BUT YOURSELF IN A
WORLD WHICH IS DOING IT'S BEST
TO MAKE YOU EVERYBODY ELSE...
♪ ♪ ♪
MEANS TO FIGHT
THE HARDEST BATTLE,
WHICH ANY HUMAN BEING
CAN FIGHT AND NEVER STOP.
DOES THIS SOUND DISMAL?
IT ISN'T.
♪ ♪ ♪
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL LIFE ON EARTH.
♪ ♪ ♪
There's little rest
for a single dad,
and back pain made it hard to
sleep and get up on time.
IT'S THE MOST
WONDERFUL LIFE ON EARTH.
Then I found Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid,
plus the 12 hour pain
relieving strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a Better AM.
>>> WELCOME TO 2020.
THAT IS AN AD PAID FOR BY THE
REPUBLICAN GROUP FOR GROWTH.
PART OF A TWO MINUTE AD FOR
IOWA.
WE HAVE THE REPUBLICAN CLUB HERE
SO TO SPEAK.
>> THAT'S CORRECT.
>> IT'S INTERESTING TO ME YOU
GUYS ARE ALREADY ATTACKING BETO
O'ROURKE.
IS IT MARCH OF 2019.
YOU'RE GOING AFTER HIM IN IOWA.
WHY ARE YOU SPENDING MONEY NOW
AGAINST BETO O'ROURKE.
>> PART OF IT IS TO SET THE
TABLE FOR WHEN HE DOES ANNOUNCE.
WE KNOW BEATO VERY WELL.
WE RAN AGAINST HIM IN THE SENATE
RACE LAST YEAR.
HE'S NOT WHAT HE PRESENTS
HIMSELF, AS A PROGRESSIVE MAN OF
THE PEOPLE.
HIS BIGGEST ACCOMPLISHMENT,
REALLY DIDN'T SUCCEED AT IT
BIGGEST THING HE WORKED ON AS A
CITY COUNCIL TRIED TO BULLDOZE
AN HISTORIC HISPANIC
NEIGHBORHOOD AND GIVE THE
PROPERTY TO HIS FATHER-IN-LAW TO
REDEVELOP.
THAT'S NOT A PROGRESSIVE.
>> THAT HE EMBODIES WHITE
PRIVILEGE, DO YOU THINK VOTERS
WILL BUY THAT?
>> IN THE MIDTERM ELECTIONS IN
EL PASO WHERE HE'S FROM, YOU HAD
A HUGE RISE IN PARTICIPATION.
IN 2014, 84,000 VOTERS WENT OUT
AND VOTED IN THE MIDTERM.
IN EL PASO, 204,000 VOTED, ONLY
10,000 DIFFERENT.
I THINK WHAT BETO DOES VERY
WELL, HE RESONATES.
HE RECOGNIZES HIS PRIVILEGE AND
TALKS ABOUT IT.
GOES INTO BLACK CHURCHES AND
SAYS THESE ARE CONVERSATIONS WE
NEED HAVE AND KNEELS AND DOES IT
IN A MORE AUTHENTIC WAY.
THAT'S WHY THE PRESIDENT WENT
DOWN AND DECIDED WHERE WOULD HE
HOLD THAT RALLY WHEN IT CAME TO
HOLDING THE WALL, NOT WHERE THE
MAJORITY ARE COMING, HE WENT TO
EL PASO.
>> I WANT TO PICK UP ON THIS
POINT YOU MADE, VERY
INTERESTING, THIS AUTHENTICITY
IDEA AND IDEAS WE HEAR FROM MANY
OF THE YOUNGER PEOPLE IN THE
PARTY, JOE BIDEN RECKONING WITH
THINGS HE DID IN THE 1970s
BECAUSE HE HAS A LONG RECORD TO
RECKON WITH TALKING ABOUT BUSING
AND DESEGREGATION.
KIMBERLY, WHAT'S YOUR
ASSESSMENT, THE COMMENTARY I
HEARD FROM MY SOURCES ON THE
PROGRESSIVE SIDE, COMMENTARY NOT
WHAT HE SAID BUT HOW HIS TEAM
HANDLE IT IN THIS MOMENT SAYING
HE DOESN'T NECESSARILY HAVE ANY
REGRETS ABOUT IT?
>> EXACTLY.
THE BIGGEST IMPEDIMENT FOR JOE
BIDEN IS THE FACT IT IS NO
LONGER FOUR YEARS AGO.
THE PARTY AND POLITICS HAVE
CHANGED DRAMATICALLY SINCE THEN.
YOU HAVE A LOT OF PEOPLE IN THE
RACE THAT DON'T HAVE THAT
BAGGAGE, DIDN'T VOTE FOR THE
IRAQ WAR LET ALONE TALK ABOUT
BUSING AND INVOLVED IN THE ANITA
HILL CLARENCE THOMAS
CONFIRMATION HEARINGS.
ALL THOSE CLIPS WILL BE BROUGHT
OUT.
HE WILL HAVE TO SPEND AS MUCH
TIME EXPLAINING HIMSELF AS
PUTTING FORTH POLICY POSITIONS
AND WILL PUT HIM AT A
DISADVANTAGE OUT OF THE GATE.
>> ARE THESE POLICY SUGAR HIGH
NAME RECOGNITION?
>> THEY ARE ALWAYS NAME
RECOGNITION AND NOT MUCH MORE
THAN THAT.
WE WILL SEE IN 6-9 MONTH.
BIDEN IS IN A TOUGH SPOT.
WHEN YOU APOLOGIZE, YOU'RE
LOSING.
APOLOGIZING IS THE WORST HE CAN
DO HOPEFULLY DEMOCRATIC VOTERS
SEE HE WAS LEGISLATING AND
MAKING POLICY 30, 40 YEARS AGO
WHEN TIMES WERE DIFFERENT AND
NOW DO THINGS DIFFERENT.
ONE THING ABOUT BIDEN AND BETO,
YOU TALK TO ANY REPUBLICAN WHO
SCARES YOU, THEY ONLY MENTION
REALLY TWO NAMES AND MAYBE A
THIRD, BIDEN AND BETO AND GET TO
A THIRD, IT'S USUALLY KAMALA
HARRIS.
>> AND PERHAPS BERNIE SANDERS, I
WILL MENTION ASIDE FROM KAMALA
HARRIS, ALL WHITE MEN.
>>> MORE FROM CASEY D.C. IN JUST
A MOMENT, KAISE, ALL FEATURED IN
THE WASHINGTON LIFE.
I WANT TO THANK WASHINGTON LIFE
FOR THAT LOVELY COVER.
BACK AFTER THIS.
I got cones,
anybody wants one!
Oh, yeah!
Get ya some!
No, I can't believe how
easy it was to save hundreds
of dollars on my car
insurance with GEICO.
Ed!
We struck sprinkles!
[cheers]
Believe it.
GEICO could save
you fifteen percent
or more on
car insurance.
This is not a bed...
it's a revolution in sleep.
The Sleep Number 360
smart bed, from $999...
senses your movement and
automatically adjusts
on each side to keep
you both comfortable.
And snoring?
How smart is that?
Smarter sleep.
So you can come out swinging,
maintain your inner
focus, and wake up rested
and ready for anything.
Only at a Sleep Number store,
save $500 on select Sleep
Number 360 smart beds.
Plus, free premium
delivery and setup.
Ends March 17th.
♪♪
Raquen...
Rakutahn...
Rakooten...
♪♪
Rakuten
Oh!
Is this my money?
Whoaaah!
Haha!
Rakuten
♪♪
Ahhh!
Rakuten!
Thanks for calling
UnitedHealthcare,
Mrs. Murphy.
Hi, I need help getting an
appointment with my podiatrist.
How's Wednesday at 2?
I can't. Dog Agility.
Thursday at 10?
Sorry. n
ñ.
Tuesday at 11?
Nope. Robot cage match.
How about the 28th at 3?
Done.
With UnitedHealthcare Medicare
Advantage plans,
including the only plans
with the AARP name,
there's so much to
take advantage of.
From scheduling appointments
to finding specialists,
it's easier to get the care
you need when you need it.
>>> A SENATE HEARING THIS WEEK
ON SEXUAL ASSAULT IN THE
MILITARY TOOK AN UNEXPECTED TURN
AFTER MARTHA McSALLY REVEALED
SHE WAS RAPED.
>> I AM A SEXUALLY ASSAULT
SURVIVOR.
UNLIKE SO MANY BRAVE SURVIVORS,
I DID NOT REPORT BEING
ASSAULTED.
LIKE SO MANY WOMEN AND MEN, I
DID NOT TRUST THE VICTIM.
I BLAMED MYSELF AND I WAS
ASHAMED AND CONFUSED AND I
THOUGHT I WAS STRONG BUT FELT
PARALYZED.
>>> THE PERPETRATORS ABUSED
THEIR POWER IN PROFOUND WAYS.
IN ONE CASE I WAS PREYED UPON
AND THEN RAPED BY A SUPERIOR
OFFICER.
I STAYED SILENT FOR MANY YEARS
BUT LATER IN MY CAREER GRAPPLING
WITH THE SCANDAL AND RESPONSES,
I FELT THE NEED TO LET PEOPLE
KNOW I, TOO, WAS A SURVIVOR.
>> McSALLY WHO WAS A FIRST WOMAN
TO FLY A COMBAT MISSION FOR THE
AIR FORCE WENT ONTO SAY WHEN SHE
REPORT THE INCIDENT, SHE WAS
DISTURBED HOW THE INCIDENT WAS
HANDLED THAT SHE NEARLY LEFT THE
MILITARY.
LAST YEAR 6,000 MEMBERS WERE
BEING ASSAULTED.
CURVING THOSE NUMBERS TO
SOMETHING SENATOR GILLIBRAND HAS
MADE HER CORNER STONE GOAL.
SHE PUT FORWARD A MEASURE THAT
WOULD TAKEN CASES OUTSIDE THE
CHAIN OF COMMAND.
GILLIBRAND PLANS TO REINTRODUCE
THAT LEGISLATION.
>> McSALLY SAYS SHE'S AGAINST
THAT APPROACH.
>> I SHARE THE DISGUST OF THE
FAILURE OF THE MILITARY SYSTEM
AND MANY COMMANDERS WHO FAILED
IN THEIR RESPONSIBILITIES.
BUT, AS FOR THIS VERY REASON
THAT WE MUST ALLOW, WE MUST
DEMAND THAT COMMANDERS STAY AT
THE CENTER OF THE SOLUTION AND
LIVE UP TO THE MORAL AND LEGAL
RESPONSIBILITIES THAT COME WITH
BEING A COMMANDER.
>> THE AIR FORCE SAYS THEY ARE
READY TO INVESTIGATE THE McSALLY
INCIDENT BUT THEY SAY McSALLY
HAVE NOT AGREED TO COOPERATE.
WHEN WE RETURN, WHAT TO WATCH
FOR IN THE WEEK AHEAD.
So in this commercial we see
two travelers
at a Comfort INN with a glow
around them,
so people watching will be like,
"Wow, maybe I'll glow too
if I book direct at
ChoiceHotels.com."
Who glows?
Just say, Badda Book.
Badda Boom.
Book now at ChoiceHotels.com.
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
What do all these people
have in common, LiMu?
[ guttural grunt ]
Exactly. Nothing!
They're completely
different people.
That's why they
make customized
car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need.
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done it again, LiMu.
[ LiMu grunts ]
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
I have a vision
correction number,
But I'm more than a number.
When I'm not sharing ideas
with my colleagues
I'm defending my kingdom.
My Essilor lenses offer more
than vision correction
with three innovative
technologies
For my ultimate in vision
Clarity
And Protection
Together in a single lens:
The Essilor Ultimate
Lens Package.
So, I can do more
of what I love!
Buy two pairs of
Essilor's best lenses
and get a $100 back instantly.
See more. Do more. Essilor
THIS BED.
>>> DAYLIGHT SAVING, NOT PLURAL.
TIME HAS NEVER SAVED US FROM
ANYTHING.
>> OUR PANEL THOUGHT THAT WAS A
REAL CONVERSATION WHEN REPLAYED
THAT IN THE BREAK.
>> NO.
ANYWAY, LET'S TALK ABOUT WHAT WE
ARE WATCHING FOR THE WEEK.
>> THE VOTE ON THE RESOLUTION OF
DISAPPROVAL FOR THE PRESIDENT'S
EMERGENCY DECLARATION IS COMING
UP IN THE SENATE.
WILL HE CHANGE MINDS?
IF NOT, THIS THING IS HEADED FOR
PASSING, HE'LL VETO IT.
>> AN ISSUE THAT WE DO NOT THINK
WOULD RESONATE REPARATIONS.
AND NOT ONLY CAN YOU USE MONEY
FOR IT, IT CAN COME IN MANY
FORMS INCLUDING TAX BREAK.
WE'LL SEE OTHER CANDIDATES GIVE
THEIR IDEA WHETHER THEY SUPPORT
IT OR NOT.
>> FURTHER ON THE DECLARATION OF
EMERGENCIES.
A LOT OF CONSERVATIVE SENATORS
ARE GOING TO VOTE AGAINST IT.
THEY LIKE THE FUNDING OF THE
WALL BUT THEY DON'T LIKE THE
ABUSE OF PRESIDENTIAL POWER.