THE PERSON WHO WOULD BRING DOWN
THIS PRESIDENCY.
NOT FOR POLITICAL REASONS.
BUT IF THERE'S ILLEGALITY IN THE
WAY OF HIS INVESTIGATION HE'LL
FIND IT, AND HE'LL PURSUE IT.
>> WHAT'S ROBERT MUELLER GOES
AFTER IS FACTS, THE LAW, AND
JUSTICE.
AND WHETHER IT'S DONALD TRUMP OR
SOME OTHER INDIVIAL, IF THE
FACTS LEAD TO THE PRESIDENT,
ROBERT MUELLER WILL PURSUE THEM.
AND IF THEY DON'T, HE WILL END
HIS INVESTIGATION.
HE DOESN'T GO AFTER ANYBODY.
HE GOES AFTER THE TRUTH.
>>> ALL THE THINGS THAT ARE
COMING OUT ABOUT THIS CASE ARE
JUST MIND-BOGGLING.
THINGS THAT YOU WOULD NEVER
BELIEVE AND YOU WOULD NEVER DO.
>> THE KILLER HAD BEEN WAITING,
A YOUNG WIFE DEAD BUT IT DIDN'T
STOP THERE.
>> SOMEBODY CAME OUT FROM BEHIND
THE TREES AND HE SHOT ME.
>> WHAT IN THE WORLD IS GOING
ON?
>> THAT'S WHAT I WANTED TO KNOW.
>> HER HUSBAND HAD AN ALIBI AND
SOMETHING ELSE, A LOVER.
>> IT WAS SHOCKING.
WOULD NEVER HAVE EXPECTED IT.
>> AND AS POLICE GOT CLOSER TO
THE TRUTH.
>> HE SAYS I THINK I KNOW WHO
DID IT.
>> THE TRUTH GOT CLOSER TO HOME.
>> HE JUST TOLD ME, HOLD ON,
IT'S ABOUT TO GET A LOT MORE
CRAZY.
>> SECRETS ON HOT SPRINGS DRIVE.
HELLO AND WELCOME TO DATELINE
EXTRA.
I'M CRAIG MELVIN.
KATE PARSONS AND BECKY SEARS
WERE BEST FRIENDS AND NEXT DOOR
NEIGHBORS.
THE TWO SHARED NEARLY
EVERYTHING, THEN KAY WAS
VICIOUSLY BEATEN IN HER OWN
HOME.
AS HER LOVED ONES REELED WITH
GRIEF INVESTIGATORS DESCRIBED
BEHIND THEIR FRIENDSHIP LAY A
TALE OF INFIDELITY AND BETRAYAL.
BUT DID DECEPTION LEAD TO
MURDER?
HERE'S DENNIS MURPHY.
>>> Reporter: YOU WON'T FIND
MAYBERRY R.F.D. ON THE MAP.
BUT IF CLOSE NEIGHBORS, GOOD
SCHOOLS, AND JUST PLAIN, OLD
CIVILITY IS WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING
FOR IN A PLACE TO CALL HOME, YOU
COULD DO WORSE THAN SETTLE IN
GROVETOWN, GEORGIA.
TAMARA BALDWIN HAS LIVED HERE
FOR 14 YEARS.
>> YOU SEE THE CHILDREN OUTSIDE
PLAYING, HAVING A GOOD TIME.
JUST A NICE, QUIET PLACE THAT
YOU WANNA MOVE AND TAKE YOUR
FAMILY TO.
>> Reporter: THE WAY WE THINK
AMERICA USED TO BE, AND SEEMS TO
BE HARDER AND HARDER TO FIND,
HUH?
>> YEAH.
>> THE ARMY'S FT. GORDON IS JUST
DOWN THE ROAD AND A NUMBER OF
THE CITY'S 12,000 RESIDENTS ARE
ACTIVE OR RETIRED MILITARY.
CRIME STATS CAN BE MEASURED IN
STOLEN BICYCLES.
>> GREAT PLACE TO RAISE A
FAMILY.
>> Reporter: HERE'S A VETERAN
INVESTIGATOR FOR THE COUNTY.
WHAT'S YOUR CRIME RATE?
>> IT'S NOT THAT HIGH.
WE DON'T HAVE TOO MUCH VIOLENT
CRIME.
>> Reporter: DOZENS OF HOMICIDES
A YEAR, WOULD YOU SAY?
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
WE MIGHT HAVE ONE A YEAR.
>> Reporter: ONE A YEAR?
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: AND IN MARCH, 2009,
THEY DID HAVE ONE -- A HOMICIDE.
A BAD ONE THAT SENT NEIGHBORS
SHOPPING FOR BURGLAR ALARMS AND
MAYBE FRESH AMMO.
>> YOU WONDER, "WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?"
>> Reporter: SO MANY TERRIBLE
THINGS HAPPENED SO QUICKLY.
SO MANY TABOOS WERE BROKEN ON AN
ANYWHERE SUBURBAN STREET THAT
THE MIND REELED.
>> WE WERE SO CONFUSED.
WE JUST KEPT PRAYING FOR THE
FAMILIES.
>> THE WHOLE NEIGHBORHOOD WAS
SHOCKED.
>> Reporter: IT BEGAN HERE WITH
TWO HOUSES, TWO BEST FRIENDS ON
A STREET CALLED HOT SPRINGS
DRIVE IN GROVETOWN.
KAY PARSONS HAD MOVED INTO THE
NEIGHBORHOOD IN 2005.
SHE WAS A DEVOTED WIFE TO HER
HUSBAND, DAVID, WHO WORKED DOWN
AT FT. GORDON.
AND AN ACTIVE LITTLE LEAGUE MOM
CHEERING ON HER 12-YEAR-OLD SON
DEREK.
TAMARA LIVED JUST DOWN THE
STREET.
>> KAY WAS A SWEETHEART.
YOU NEVER SAW HER UPSET, NEVER
SAW HER MAD, ALWAYS SMILING,
JUST A JOY TO BE AROUND.
>> WHAT KINDS OF THINGS DID SHE
LIKE TO DO?
>> WELL, MOSTLY ANYTHING DEALING
WITH HER SON AND HER HUSBAND.
SHE WAS VERY SUPPORTIVE, ALWAYS
BEING WITH THEM.
>> Reporter: NEXT DOOR TO KAY
LIVED BECKY SEARS.
BECKY HAD HER HANDS FULL, TOO.
SHE AND HER HUSBAND TONY HAD
FIVE KIDS, INCLUDING TWO OLDER
SONS FROM BECKY'S FIRST
MARRIAGE.
TAMARA BALDWIN:
>> SHE'S ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE
WHO'S VERY OUTGOING, ONE OF
THOSE, "HEY, HOW YOU DOING,"
TYPE PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: TAMARA GOT TO KNOW
BOTH, BUT SAYS KAY AND BECKY
REALLY HIT IT OFF.
>> THEY WERE BEST FRIENDS.
THEY WERE BASICALLY INSEPARABLE.
AND THEY WERE TOGETHER
24/7 ALMOST.
>> Reporter: THE TWO NEIGHBORS
BECAME PEAS IN A POD.
THEY WORKED AT THE SAME PHYSICAL
THERAPY CENTER CALLED
HEALING HANDS.
>> THEY'D GO ON VACATIONS WITH
EACH OTHER.
>> Reporter: JURGEN COWLING WAS
THEIR BOSS.
>> WHEN YOU THINK OF THEM BEING
AROUND YOUR OFFICE, WHAT DO YOU
SEE THEM DOING?
>> WELL, WE ALL GET ALONG.
AND KAY AND, YOU KNOW, YOU KNEW
THEY WERE BEST FRIENDS, 'CAUSE
THEY WERE CUTTING UP ON EACH
OTHER.
AND THEN THEY WOULD ALSO TELL
STORIES ABOUT THEIR SONS'
BASEBALL, ESPECIALLY DURING THE
BASEBALL SEASONS, 'CAUSE THEY
WERE BEST FRIENDS, THE SONS.
>> Reporter: KAY AND BECKY EVEN
JOINED WEIGHT WATCHERS TOGETHER.
AND THE TWO OF THEM WERE PRETTY
COMPETITIVE AT THE WEIGHT
WATCHER THING, HUH?
>> YES, YES.
>> Reporter: WHO'S UP A POUND,
WHO'S DOWN A POUND?
>> YES.
EVERY DAY.
>> Reporter: AND ONE DAY IN
MARCH, 2009, BEGAN LIKE ANY
OTHER.
KAY, THE LITTLE LEAGUE MOM, GOT
UP TO TAKE DEREK TO SCHOOL, AND
BECKY, THE MOTHER OF FIVE, LEFT
HER HOUSE A FEW MINUTES LATER TO
DROP OFF HER KIDS BEFORE HER
WORK DAY BEGAN.
ALL VERY ROUTINE.
UNTIL 8:30 A.M., WHEN CONTRACTOR
MITCH COZART SHOWED UP TO DO
SOME MAINTENANCE WORK ON KAY'S
BACK DOOR.
YOU'RE COMING AROUND THE CORNER.
YOU LIFT UP THE LATCH GATE.
AND TELL ME WHAT YOU SEE.
>> OKAY.
WHEN I WALKED BACK INTO THE --
INTO -- WHERE THE BACK DOOR WAS,
IT WAS -- THE GLASS WAS BUSTED
OUT.
AND -- I -- I IMMEDIATELY KNEW
THEY HAD BEEN BROKEN INTO.
>> Reporter: DID YOU PUT YOUR
HEAD INSIDE THE HOUSE AND LOOK
AROUND OR CALL --
>> ALL I DID --
>> Reporter: -- CALL OUT HER
NAME.
>> I JUST -- I JUST STUCK MY
HEAD JUST INSIDE JUST ENOUGH TO
HOLLER OUT FOR HER.
AND I -- I DIDN'T GET NO
RESPONSE.
>> Reporter: HE TRIED CALLING
KAY'S PHONE.
NO ANSWER THERE EITHER.
HE CAME BACK OUT FRONT AND
NOTICED A YOUNG MAN SITTING ON A
ROCK ACROSS THE STREET.
HIS NAME WAS MICHAEL, THE OLDEST
OF KAY'S FRIEND BECKY'S FIVE
KIDS.
MICHAEL HAD OVERHEARD THE
CONTRACTOR TALKING ON THE PHONE.
>> I WALKED UP TO HIM.
AND I SAID, "HEY, DID YOU SAY
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS HOUSE BEING
BROKEN INTO?"
AND HE WAS, LIKE, "YEAH."
AND I WAS, LIKE, "WELL, MINE HAS
BEEN, TOO."
>> Reporter: SO NOW TWO BROAD
DAYLIGHT BREAK-INS OF ACROSS THE
FENCE NEIGHBORS.
WAS THE THIEF STILL LURKING?
>> I CARRY A FIREARM IN MY
VEHICLE.
SO -- AND SO ACTUALLY I -- I
WENT OUT AND GOT ONE JUST IN
CASE.
YOU KNOW, THE -- I MEAN, THE --
SOMEBODY COULD RUN OUT OR
WHATEVER.
>> Reporter: HE CALLED 911.
>> YEAH, THE BACK DOOR IS BROKE
IN AND THE NEXT DOOR NEIGHBOR'S
DOOR IS BROKE IN.
I'D CALLED THE OWNER, BUT SHE'S
NOT HERE.
AND I DON'T THINK -- IF SHE'S
GONE.
I MEAN, I HOLLERED INTO THE
DOOR.
>> UH-HUH.
>> AND I DIDN'T GET NO RESPONSE.
>> YEAH, I DON'T WANT YOU TO GO
IN.
>> Reporter: THE CONTRACTOR
FOLLOWED INSTRUCTIONS, AND
WITHIN MINUTES, LAW ENFORCEMENT
RESPONDED TO THE SCENE READY TO
INVESTIGATE TWO POTENTIAL
BURGLARIES RIGHT NEXT DOOR TO
EACH OTHER.
POLICE TAPED OFF THE AREA.
NOW TAMARA'S NEIGHBORS WERE
CALLING HER AT WORK, INCLUDING
KAY'S HUSBAND DAVID.
HE WAS TRAVELING ON BUSINESS.
>> HE ASKED ME, "HAVE YOU SPOKEN
TO KAY?"
AND I'M, LIKE, "NO, NOT TODAY.
I'M AT WORK."
AND HE SAYS, "OKAY, I'M JUST
TRYING TO GET IN TOUCH WITH KAY.
I'M IN CALIFORNIA."
>> Reporter: FIRST RESPONDERS AT
THE SCENE ALERTED INVESTIGATOR
JIMMY EDMUNDS WITH THE COLUMBIA
COUNTY SHERIFF'S OFFICE.
>> IT'S VERY UNUSUAL TO HAVE --
HAVE TWO HOUSES SIDE BY SIDE,
YOU KNOW, HIT IT ONE TIME
THAT'S, YOU KNOW, THAT SAME WAY.
>> Reporter: SO ARE YOU
THINKING, "WHERE'S THIS GUY
GONNA GO NEXT?"
>> CORRECT.
I'M DEFINITELY THINKING,
"WHERE'S HE AT?"
>> Reporter: BUT AS EDMUNDS
TURNED HIS ATTENTION TO THE
BREAK-INS AT THESE TWO HOMES, HE
AND HIS TEAM DISCOVERED
SOMETHING UGLY.
>> SHE WAS IN A POOL OF BLOOD.
>> Reporter: THIS WASN'T GOING
TO BE A SIMPLE BURGLARY.
THIS WAS A VIOLENT ATTACK WITH A
BLOODY TRAIL BETWEEN THE HOMES
OF TWO BEST FRIENDS AND A FEMALE
BODY LYING IN THE GARAGE.
>> SHE WAS BEATEN SO SEVERELY
YOU COULDN'T EVEN RECOGNIZE HER.
>> Reporter: WHAT HAD HAPPENED
ON HOT SPRINGS DRIVE?
AND WHOSE SANCTUARY WAS ABOUT TO
BE VIOLATED NEXT?
>> A BADLY-INJURED VICTIM IN ONE
HOUSE.
INVESTIGATORS WONDER WAS
SOMETHING WORSE WAITING FOR THEM
NEXT DOOR?
>> COMING UP --
>> THE POINT OF ENTRY YOU COULD
SEE THE BACK DOOR WAS THERE.
>> WHEN SECRETS ON HOT SPRINGS
DRIVE CONTINUES.
S THERE.
>> WHEN SECRETS ON HOT SPRINGS
DRIVE CONTINUES.
you should defie
how GEICO
could help you save on
homeowners insurance.
Nice tip. I'll give you two
bucks for the chair.
Two?! That's a Victorian
antique!
All right, how much for the
recliner, then?
Wait wait... how did that get
out here?
That is definitely not for sale!
Is this a yard sale?
If it's in the yard then it's...
for sale.
Oh, here we go.
GEICO. It's easy to switch
and save
on homeowners and renters
insurance.
You wouldn't accept
an incomplete job
from any one else.
Why accept it from
your allergy pills?
Flonase Sensimist relieves
all your worst symptoms,
including nasal congestion,
which most pills don't.
And all from a gentle mist
you can barely feel.
Flonase Sensim
With tough food, your dentures
may slip and fall.
Fixodent Ultra-Max Hold
gives you the strongest hold
ever
to lock your dentures.
So now you can eat tough food
without worry.
Fixodent and forget it.
>> Reporter: MARCH 25, 2009.
JUST AFTER 9AM.
SHERIFF'S DEPUTIES HAD RUSHED TO
THIS QUIET RESIDENTIAL STREET IN
GROVETOWN, GEORGIA TO
INVESTIGATE NOT ONE, BUT TWO
BURGLARIES.
WORRIED ABOUT HER FRIENDS AND
NEIGHBORS KAY AND BECKY,
TAMARA BALDWIN LEFT WORK AND
HEADED HOME TO WHAT SHOCKINGLY
HAD BECOME A CRIME SCENE.
>> DID YOU SEE LOTS OF VEHICLES
AND UNIFORMS AND --
>> A LOT OF POLICE CARS, THE
ENTIRE CORNER WAS ALL TAPED OFF
WITH CRIME TAPE.
NOW YOU SEE TWO HOUSES THAT I
HAVE TO PASS TO GET HOME, AND
YOU WONDER WHAT'S GOIN' ON.
>> Reporter: AND WHAT THE
RESPONDERS FOUND INSIDE THESE
HOMES WOULD PUT THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD INTO FULL-ON PANIC
MODE.
INVESTIGATOR JIMMY EDMUNDS
ENTERED THE HOME OF KAY, THE
LITTLE LEAGUE MOM, THROUGH THAT
SHATTERED GLASS BACK DOOR, THE
ONE THE CONTRACTOR FIRST
NOTICED.
THEN EDMUNDS SAW IT: A TRAIL OF
BLOOD.
>> IMMEDIATELY, I COULD START
SEEIN' SPOTS OF BLOOD ON THE
FLOOR.
I COULD SEE AN EMPTY COFFEE CUP
THAT HAD SPILLED RIGHT THERE ON
THE FLOOR FROM, FROM MCDONALD'S.
>> THERE WAS A MCDONALD'S BAG
ON -- FOOD BAG ON THE FLOOR AND
A PURSE.
AND I STARTED SEEIN' SIGNS OF
BLOOD ON -- ON THE SOFA IN THE
LIVING ROOM, ON THE -- ON THE
CARPET.
AND THEN YOU GO INTO THE FOYER
AREA, WHERE THERE WAS A LOT OF
BLOOD ON THE WALLS, ON THE DOOR,
ON THE FLOOR.
>> SO THIS IS SUGGESTING A
MOVING STRUGGLE.
>> DEFINITELY.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE HOMEOWNER CAME
HOME AND SURPRISED A BURGLAR IN
HER HOUSE, AND A STRUGGLE ENSUED
WHERE SHE WAS BEATEN.
>> Reporter: THE BLOODY PATH LED
EDMUNDS FURTHER INTO THE HOUSE,
TO A BLOODY HAND PRINT ON THE
DOOR OUT TO THE PARSONS' GARAGE.
>> AND YOU CAN TELL THERE WAS --
THERE WAS MORE BEATING GOIN' ON
IN THE GARAGE.
THERE WAS BLOOD SPATTER ON THE
WALLS.
SO SHE WAS ALREADY BLEEDING
BEFORE SHE GOT INTO THE GARAGE.
>> Reporter: AND THAT'S WHERE
THIS APPARENT STRUGGLE HAD
ENDED.
THE DEPUTIES FOUND 41-YEAR OLD
KAY PARSONS LYING THERE ON THE
FLOOR.
>> HAD YOU EVER SEEN A SCENE
LIKE THAT?
>> NOTHING -- NOTHING THAT
DRASTIC, NO.
SHE WAS BEATEN SO SEVERELY IN
HER HEAD, IT WAS PRETTY BAD.
>> Reporter: BUT AMAZINGLY, KAY
WAS ALIVE.
EMT'S HURRIED HER TO THE
HOSPITAL, HER LIFE HANGING BY A
THREAD.
>> SHE STILL HAD A HEARTBEAT.
>> BUT SHE WAS IN A VERY BAD
WAY.
>> VERY, VERY BAD WAY.
>> Reporter: INVESTIGATOR
EDMUNDS MADE THE CALL TO ALERT
KAY'S HUSBAND.
>> HE WAS IN LOS ANGELES FOR
WORK.
I WAS ABLE TO TALK TO HIM ON THE
PHONE, LET HIM KNOW HE NEEDED TO
COME BACK HERE AS QUICK AS
SA
POSSIBLE.
>> SO HOW DID HE TAKE THAT NEWS?
>> HE WAS -- HE WAS PRETTY
DEVASTATED.
I TRIED NOT TO TELL HIM ON THE
PHONE.
I TRIED TO TELL HIM, YOU KNOW,
"I NEED -- YOU NEED TO COME
BACK.
THERE'S BEEN AN ACCIDENT," YOU
KNOW?
BUT HE -- HE GUESSED PRETTY MUCH
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
>> Reporter: KAY'S HUSBAND DAVID
BOOKED A FLIGHT HOME, AS
INVESTIGATORS TURNED THEIR
ATTENTION TO THE HOUSE NEXT
DOOR.
THAT'S WHERE KAY'S FRIEND BECKY
THE MOTHER WITH FIVE KIDS LIVED.
COULD THERE BE ANOTHER VICTIM
THERE?
>> THE POINT OF ENTRY WE COULD
SEE WAS THE BACKDOOR ALSO THERE,
AND WE FOUND SPOTS OF BLOOD ON
THE BACK DOOR.
>> Reporter: INSIDE, BECKY'S
PLACE WAS RANSACKED, BUT, QUICK
RELIEF, AS THEY LOOKED AROUND
THERE WERE NO NEW VICTIMS.
THE BLOOD SMEARS THEY'D NOTED
APPEARED TO BE FROM THE CRIME
SCENE NEXT DOOR.
>> THAT MEANS YOU HAVE SOMEBODY
THAT IS BRAVE ENOUGH, OR JUST --
OR JUST CRUEL ENOUGH TO JUST --
JUST BEAT THIS WOMAN SO
SEVERELY, AND THEN IS GONNA GO
NEXT DOOR AND COMMIT ANOTHER
BURGLARY?
>> Reporter: BECKY HAD BEEN AT
WORK THAT MORNING WITH HER
19-YEAR OLD SON CHRISTOPHER.
THE TWO OF THEM RACED HOME TO
THE SCENE AND MET UP WITH HER
OLDER SON MICHAEL.
>> THEY'RE BOTH THERE, SO YOUR
MOTHER AND CHRISTOPHER ARE
THERE?
>> YEAH, THEY PULLED UP TOGETHER
AT THE SAME TIME, WITH COLUMBIA
COUNTY OFFICER.
WE ALL WALK AROUND BACK TO KAY'S
HOUSE, AND MY MOM, SHE SOUNDS
VERY DISTRAUGHT.
SHE'S -- SHE'S SCREAMIN' KAY'S
NAME.
>> SHE SHOWS UP AT HER HOUSE
WHILE YOU WERE ALL IN THE
BACKYARD THERE?
>> RIGHT.
THEY SHOW UP ON SCENE AND -- AND
THEY'RE, WONDERING WHAT'S GOING
ON, AND THEY'RE -- THEY'RE
PRETTY -- PRETTY SHAKEN UP.
>> Reporter: EVERYONE ELSE IN
BECKY'S FAMILY WAS ACCOUNTED
FOR, HER HUSBAND TONY, A LONG
HAUL TRUCKER, WAS AWAY ON THE
ROAD, HER THREE YOUNGER CHILDREN
WERE FINE AT SCHOOL AND DAY
CARE.
THE INVESTIGATOR SAID BECKY'S
FOCUS THEN TURNED TO KAY.
>> UNDERSTANDABLY SHE WAS UPSET.
YOU KNOW, SHE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED TO HER NEIGHBOR.
SHE JUST KNEW HER NEIGHBOR
HAD -- HAD LEFT IN AN AMBULANCE.
>> Reporter: AND IN FACT,
EDMUNDS SAYS, BECKY WAS LESS
CONCERNED ABOUT THAT BURGLARY IN
HER OWN HOME AND MORE ANXIOUS TO
GET TO SEE HER NEIGHBOR.
MICHELLE AMERSON IS A LONGTIME
FRIEND OF BECKY WHO ALSO LIVED
NEARBY.
HER SISTER DROVE BECKY TO THE
HOSPITAL.
>> SHE GOT TO THE HOSPITAL, YOU
KNOW, SHE WAS DEMANDING TO GET
TO SEE HER FRIEND.
>> SHE GO TO BEDSIDE FOR KAY,
HUH?
>> YEAH, SHE WANTED TO GET
THERE.
>> I SAID, "WHAT HOSPITAL DID
THEY GO TO?"
>> Reporter: NEWS OF THE ATTACK
QUICKLY SPREAD TO ANOTHER CLOSE
FRIEND OF KAY'S,
SUZANNE FRAZIER.
>> I HUNG UP THE PHONE AND I WAS
SHAKIN', AND SO, I CALLED MY
BOSS AND I SAID, "I GOTTA GO, I
GOTTA GO."
AND I LEFT.
>> BROKE SOME -- BROKE SOME
LAWS, HUH?
>> I RAN RED LIGHTS, I FLEW.
I MEAN, I JUST WENT.
>> Reporter: TAMARA RUSHED TO
THE HOSPITAL TOO.
>> DID YOU GET TO HER BEDSIDE
OR --
>> NO.
>>  -- BE ABLE TO TAKE --
>>  -- A LOOK IN?
>> I DID NOT.
I -- I JUST STAYED IN THE
WAITING ROOM.
THERE WERE A WHOLE LOTTA OTHER
PEOPLE IN THE WAITING ROOM.
>> BUT THE PROGNOSIS WAS VERY
BAD, WASN'T IT?
MACHINES WERE --
>> YEAH.
>>  --KEEPING HER ALIVE AT THAT
POINT EVEN, HUH?
>> YES.
>> Reporter: THE FRIENDS ALL
KEPT AN EDGY VIGIL FOR NEWS
ABOUT KAY'S CONDITION, WAITING
FOR HER HUSBAND TO GET TO HER
BEDSIDE.
LIVES ALL CHANGED IN AN INSTANT.
A HOME INVASION AND BURGLARY IN
BROAD DAYLIGHT.
A WOMAN FIGHTING FOR HER LIFE.
AND NOW A PERPETRATOR ON THE
LOOSE.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW WHETHER YOU
HAVE A GUY ON THE MOVE WHO COULD
BE READY TO BUST INTO ANOTHER
HOUSE ALONG HERE, RIGHT?
>> EXACTLY, EXACTLY.
WE DON'T KNOW IF WE HAD A MAD
MAN ON THE LOOSE HERE, YOU KNOW?
>> YOU SETTIN' UP SECURITY ON
THESE STREETS?
>> ON EVERY ONE OF THESE
STREETS, WE'RE GOIN' TO EVERY
ONE OF THESE HOUSES.
WE'RE STOPPIN' ANYTHING THAT
COMES IN OR COMES OUT OF THIS
WHOLE NEIGHBORHOOD, WE'RE
TALKING TO EVERYBODY.
>> IT'S YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD.
AND --
>> YEAH.
>> THERE'S SOMEBODY OUT THERE
WHO'S APPARENTLY A VERY VIOLENT
PERSON.
>> YES.
>> YOU GOTTA BE TERRIBLY SCARED.
>> I WAS.
I'M THINKING THAT THERE'S
SOMEONE WHO'S WALKIN' AROUND THE
NEIGHBORHOOD WATCHING AND SEEING
WHEN PEOPLE ARE LEAVIN' AND
BASICALLY ATTACKING OR --
>> Reporter: ON HOT SPRINGS
DRIVE, THE INVESTIGATORS KNEW
THEY HAD A SERIOUS CRIME ON
THEIR HANDS, BUT AS THEY LEARNED
MORE FROM THAT BLOODY SCENE, THE
SHOCKWAVES ONLY KEPT ROLLING.
COMING UP --
>> HE SAID, "OH GOD.
NO, NO, KAY."
>> A HUSBAND RETURNS HOME TO
TRAGEDY AND QUESTIONS.
>> I JUST GOT A WEIRD FEELING.
SOMETHING WASN'T RIGHT.
>> WHEN SECRETS ON HOT SPRINGS
DRIVE CONTINUES.
N SECRETS ON HOS
-We're doing karaoke later,
and you're gonna sing.
-Jamie, this is your house?
-I know, it's not much,
but it's home.
Right, kids?
-Kids?
-Papa, Papa!
-[ Laughs ]
-You didn't tell me
your friends were coming.
-Oh, yeah.
-This one is tiny like a child.
-Yeah, she is.
Oh, but seriously,
it's good to be surrounded
by what matters most --
a home and auto bundle
from Progressive.
-Oh, sweetie,
please, play for us.
-Oh, no, I couldn't.
-Please.
-Okay.
[ Singing in Spanish ]
-Please.
-Okay.
I love my babies,
love my boys.
Since I'm a truck driver,
you know there's times
that I'm gone for,
like, three weeks at a time.
Even if I'm 3,000 miles away,
I'm connected with my boys.
Every day I can
video chat with them.
I could be in the middle
of Wyoming.
Even if I'm like waaay...
out here,
I can still reach my kids.
Baby, you-- you see me?
(sons)
Hey, Daddy!
(VO)
There for you
when it matters most.
Unlimited on the best network
now comes with
Apple Music on us.
Get a free Galaxy S10e
when you buy the new Galaxy S10.
Only on Verizon.
We switched.
I switched to Chevy.
We switched to Chevy.
I switched from
a Ram to a Chevy.
See why people
are switching to Chevy.
We love our Chevy.
Why did we switch?
Just look at it.
Switch into a
new Chevy today.
Current competitive owners
get 21% below MSRP on most
Equinox models when
financing with GM Financial.
That's over $8,300
on THIS Equinox.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
IT WAS A GHASTLY CRIME.
SUBURBAN MOM KAK PARSONS HAD
BEEN SAVAGELY BEATEN DURING WHAT
LOOKED LIKE A HEME INVASION
LEAVING A BLOODY TRAIL.
THE SUSPECTED BURGLAR THAN
RANSACKED THE HOUSE NEXT DOOR.
KAY WAS FIGHTING FOR HER LIFE IN
THE HOSPITAL WHILE POLICE WERE
SWEEPING THE HOUSE FOR CLUES.
WHAT HAD HAPPENED IN THAT HOUSE,
AND COULD THEY CATCH KAY'S
ATTACKER BEFORE THEY STRUCK
AGAIN?
RETURNING TO OUR STORY HERE'S
DENNIS MURPHY.
>> Reporter: FRIENDS AND FAMILY
GATHERED AT THE HOSPITAL KEEPING
A VIGIL FOR KAY PARSONS, A
SUBURBAN MOM WHO'D BEEN BRUTALLY
BEATEN THAT MORNING IN A HOME
INVASION.
AND WHILE HER NEXT-DOOR NEIGHBOR
BECKY'S HOME HAD BEEN
BURGLARIZED TOO, BECKY DIDN'T
SEEM TO CARE AS MUCH ABOUT THAT.
GOOD FRIEND TAMARA SAYS THAT FOR
BECKY, IT WAS ALL ABOUT GETTING
TO SEE KAY.
>> SHE CONTINUES TO ASK IF
"WELL, CAN WE GO IN AND SEE HER?
CAN WE GO IN AND SEE HER?"
THEY TELL US NO.
>> Reporter: EVENTUALLY, ONE OF
KAY'S CLOSEST FRIENDS
SUZANNE FRAZIER DID GET BACK TO
HER BEDSIDE.
>> COULD YOU RECOGNIZE HER IF
YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT IT WAS HER?
>> NOT REALLY, NOT REALLY.
>> ALL PUFFED UP?
>> VERY -- VERY -- FACE WAS VERY
FULL.
HEAD WRAPPED.
SO I ASKED THE NURSE, SAID, "IS
SHE BRAIN DEAD?"
AND SHE DIDN'T ANSWER ME.
>> Reporter: KAY WAS JUST
CLINGING TO LIFE, SOME WRENCHING
DECISIONS HAD TO BE MADE.
AND DOCTORS WERE WAITING FOR
GUIDANCE FROM HER HUSBAND DAVID,
WHO ARRIVED BACK FROM A BUSINESS
TRIP IN CALIFORNIA.
>> HOW DID DAVID SEEM, THE
HUSBAND?
>> HE SEEMED VERY DISTRAUGHT.
HE SEEMED VERY UPSET.
>> YOU COULD HEAR HIM SCREAMIN'
THROUGH THE DOUBLE DOORS.
AND HE SAID, "OH, GOD, NO, NO,
KAY."
>> Reporter: INVESTIGATOR
EDMUNDS SAW DAVID TOO.
AND LAW ENFORCEMENT TENDS TO SEE
THINGS A LITTLE DIFFERENTLY,
ESPECIALLY WITH HUSBANDS.
>> AT THE HOSPITAL, YOU MEET HIM
IN PERSON, YOU SEE HIM?
>> RIGHT.
HIS WIFE'S ON LIFE SUPPORT, YOU
KNOW.
AND HE'S PRETTY DISTRAUGHT.
BUT I JUST, STILL, I JUST GOT A
WEIRD FEELING.
SOMETHING WASN'T RIGHT.
I COULDN'T TELL IF IT WAS,
OVERBOARD OR IF IT WAS JUST -- I
COULDN'T PUT MY FINGER ON IT BUT
THERE WAS SOMETHING THAT WAS
BOTHERING ME.
>> Reporter: SO EVEN THOUGH THE
HUSBAND HAD AN ALIBI, THAT OUT
OF STATE BUSINESS TRIP.
>> HE'S ON YOUR RADAR AND YOU
BOTH KNOW THAT?
>> YES.
SO I'M WATCHING HIM PRETTY,
PRETTY CLOSE.
>> Reporter: BY THAT POINT
EDMUNDS WAS TRYING TO DETERMINE
EXACTLY WHAT HAD HAPPENED ON HOT
SPRINGS DRIVE.
HE HAD HIS TEAM TAKE PICTURES OF
KAY, COLLECTING ANY PHYSICAL
EVIDENCE FROM THAT CONFRONTATION
IN THE HOUSE.
AND THEY CAME UP WITH SOMETHING,
A BIT OF HUMAN HAIR FOUND UNDER
KAY'S FINGERNAILS.
IT JUST MIGHT BE FROM HER
ATTACKER.
>> SHE HAD DEFENSE WOUNDS TO
HER -- TO HER ARMS, TO HER
HANDS.
SHE WAS -- YOU KNOW, BRUISES
EVERYWHERE, ALL OVER HER BODY.
>> Reporter: ALL INDICATING
SOMETHING ELSE, KAY HAD FOUGHT
BACK.
AND WHOEVER ASSAULTED HER HAD
BEEN ON THE PROWL FOR SOMETHING.
DEPUTIES SHOT VIDEO OF THE
UPSTAIRS BEDROOM.
IT HAD BEEN LOOTED, WITH JEWELRY
AND OTHER VALUABLES MISSING.
AND THEY FOUND WHAT SEEMED LIKE
A SIMILAR M.O. IN BECKY'S HOUSE
NEXT DOOR.
>> THE MASTER BEDROOM IN THAT
RESIDENCE HAD BEEN RANSACKED.
>> SO BOTH HOUSES HAD BEEN
TOSSED.
>> BOTH HOUSES.
>> Reporter: BECKY'S MOST
VALUABLE NECKLACE AND RINGS,
GONE.
AND AS EDMUNDS KEPT EXAMINING
THAT GRISLY SCENE IN THE
PARSONS' GARAGE, HE DETERMINED
HOW THE BURGLAR HAD ASSAULTED
KAY, WITH A HAMMER, FOUND
UNDERNEATH THE CAR, AND A
BASEBALL BAT.
>> SO THE WAY THE WEAPONS THE
APPEARED JUST DESCRIBE A
HORRENDOUS ATTACK?
>> YES, IT APPEARED THAT THIS --
THIS HAMMER, YOU KNOW, WAS USED
IN - - IN, THERE WAS SO MUCH
BLOOD, IT -- IT SLIPPED OUTTA
THE ATTACKER'S HAND.
AND, YOU KNOW, THE BASEBALL BAT,
WHICH WE WERE ABLE TO DETERMINE
BELONGED AT THAT HOUSE, WAS --
WAS A WEAPON OF OPPORTUNITY
AFTER HE LOST THE FIRST WEAPON.
>> Reporter: IT LOOKED LIKE THE
LITTLE LEAGUE MOM WAS BEATEN
WITH HER OWN SON DEREK'S
BASEBALL BAT.
>> IT REALLY TOUCHED MY SOUL
KNOWING HOW MUCH DEREK LOVED
BASEBALL.
AND I'M, LIKE, "HOW IN THE WORLD
COULD SOMEONE TAKE A BASEBALL
BAT AND, YOU KNOW, BEAT HER?"
>> Reporter: AN OLD-FASHIONED
DRAGNET REMAINED DRAWN AROUND
THE SUBDIVISION.
FIND THE ATTACKER.
>> YOU GOT A CRAZY GUY ON YOUR
HANDS.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
I MEAN, HE -- HE -- HE BEAT THAT
WOMAN SEVERELY, AND WE NEED TO
FIND WHO IT WAS AND WHERE HE WAS
AND -- AND GET HIM OFF THE
STREET.
>> Reporter: SOME RESIDENTS
MENTIONED A MYSTERIOUS FIGURE
THEY HAD SEEN RECENTLY.
>> WE HEARD ABOUT A GUY THAT --
THAT -- SUPPOSEDLY A HOMELESS
GUY THAT WAS LIVIN' IN THE WOODS
AROUND THERE SOMEWHERE.
>> Reporter: SO THE INVESTIGATOR
DISPATCHED SOME DEPUTIES TO
CHECK OUT THE AREA JUST A FEW
HUNDRED FEET FROM KAY'S HOUSE.
>> WE CHECKED THE WOODS.
WE DIDN'T SEE ANY SIGNS OF
ANYBODY LIVIN' THERE, ANYTHING
OF THAT NATURE. AND WE REALLY
COULDN'T PROVE OR DISPROVE THERE
WAS ANYBODY THAT WAS LIVIN' IN
THE WOODS THERE.
>> Reporter: SO A POTENTIAL
LEAD, DASHED.
BUT INVESTIGATORS HAD ANOTHER.
UNLIKELY AS IT MAY SEEM, TINY
GROVETOWN, GEORGIA HAS A FEW
'USUAL SUSPECTS,' INCLUDING A
YOUNG MAN WHO LIVED JUST AROUND
THE CORNER FROM KAY PARSONS'
HOME.
>> WE LOOK AT OUR NEIGHBORHOOD
AND SEE WHO'S LIVIN' AROUND
THERE.
AND WE, YOU KNOW, WE HAD A
FREQUENT FLYER IN THERE THAT --
>> A WHO?
>> A FREQUENT FLYER, YOU KNOW.
THAT -- THAT'S SOMEBODY THAT WE
DEAL WITH ALL THE TIME.
YOU KNOW, THAT -- THAT COMMIT
THE SAME TYPE OF CRIMES, YOU
KNOW.
WE KNEW THIS GUY.
WE -- WE'VE ARRESTED HIM SEVERAL
TIMES FOR BURGLARIES.
AND HE LIVES CLOSE BY IN THE
AREA.
>> SO IF A COMPUTER'S MISSING OR
A PIECE OF JEWELRY'S GONE
ASTRAY?
>> IF THERE'S CARS BROKEN
INTO --
>> YOU GO TO YOUR FREQUENT FLYER
AND ASK HIM WHAT HE KNOWS ABOUT
IT, HUH?
>> IF HE'S CLOSE BY, WE -- WE
DEFINITELY TALK TO HIM.
>> SO IN THIS CASE, ON THAT DAY,
YOU DO THAT, HUH?
>> WE DO.
BUT WE WERE -- WE WERE ABLE TO
QUICKLY RULE HIM OUT.
HE -- HE HAD AN ALIBI.
THERE WAS NO WAY HE COULD BE
THERE.
>> Reporter: THEN FROM THE
HOSPITAL, THE NEWS EVERYONE
FEARED AND EXPECTED.
DOCTORS DETERMINED KAY'S
INJURIES WERE TOO SEVERE FOR HER
TO MAKE IT.
THE FAMILY DECIDED TO TAKE HER
OFF LIFE SUPPORT.
KAY PARSONS, DEVOTED WIFE TO
DAVID, LOVING MOTHER TO DEREK,
WAS GONE.
>> AND SO THEN THEY LET ME KNOW
THAT SHE HAD PASSED AWAY.
>> YOU LOST YOUR FRIEND, KAY.
YES.
YEP.
>> A BEATING DEATH, A BREAK-IN.
>> YES.
>> HOW HORRIBLE IS THIS FOR YOU,
SUZANNE?
>> ONE OF THE WORST DAYS OF MY
LIFE.
I DIDN'T EXPECT IT.
41 YEARS OLD.
I MEAN, YOU CAN SEE SOMEBODY
DYING OF CANCER OR, YOU KNOW, IN
A CAR WRECK OR SOMETHING LIKE
THAT, BUT TO BE BEATEN BEYOND
ANYTHING.
>> DID YOU GO BACK?
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
>> YOU SAID GOODBYE TO KAY?
>> AS MUCH AS I COULD.
>> Reporter: NOW THE STAKES
QUICKLY BECAME MUCH HIGHER FOR
THIS INVESTIGATION.
KAY PARSONS HAD BEEN MURDERED.
AND EDMUNDS STARTED THINKING
THIS KILLER MIGHT JUST BE
SOMEONE WHO KNEW BOTH WOMEN,
BECKY AND KAY.
SOMEONE WHO HAD BEEN RIGHT THERE
AT THE SCENE OF THE CRIME.
COMING UP --
POLICE TAKE A CLOSER LOOK AT
BECKY'S SON MICHAEL.
>> THEY'RE NOT SEEING THE NEXT
DOOR BOY SITTING ON A ROCK
ACROSS THE STREET.
AND THAT MADE ME SUSPICIOUS.
>> HE DISCOVERS HIS MOTHER'S
HOUSE BROKEN INTO.
HE'S ON THE SCENE WHEN WE GET
THERE.
SO THAT RAISED A LOT OF RED
FLAGS.
>> WHEN SECRETS ON HOT SPRINGS
DRIVE CONTINUES.
FLAGS.
>> WHEN SECRETS ON HOT SPRINGS
DRIVE CONTINUES.
All money managers might
seem the same,
but some give their clients
cookie cutter portfolios.
Fisher Investments tailors
portfolios
to your goals and needs.
Some only call when they have
something to sell.
Fisher calls regularly so
you stay informed.
And while some advisors are
happy to earn commissions
whether you do well or not.
Fisher Investments fees
are structured so we do better
when you do better.
Maybe that's why most
of our clients
come from other money managers.
Fisher Investments. Clearly
better money management.
If Old Spice Sweat Defense
helps keep me feeling dry,
how will they
know I worked hard?
I've gotta make stuff harder.
♪
There, that's hard.
Termites,
feasting on homes 24/7.
We're on the move.
♪
Roger.
Hey Rick, all good?
Oh yeah, we're good.
We're good.
Termites never stop trying to
get in,
we never stop working to keep
them out.
Terminix.
Defenders of Home.
>>> WITH YOUR TOP STORIES.
AXIOS REPORTS THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP WADED INTO CONTROVERSY
DURING A SPEECH FOR RNC DONORS
AT MAR-A-LAGO ON FRIDAY.
THREE PEOPLE THE PRESIDENT
CLAIMED SAID DEMOCRATS QUOTE
SAID DEMOCRATS HATE JEWISH
PEOPLE.
THIS WAS IN RESPONSE TO
ANTI-SEMITIC CLAIMS FROM
CONGRESSWOMAN OMAR.
>>> 157 PEOPLE WERE KILLED
ABOARD AN ETHIOPIAN AIRLINES
FLIGHT.
BACK TO DATELINE.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO DATELINE
EXTRA.
I'M CRAIG MELVIN.
INVESTIGATORS LOOKED INTO
REPORTS OF A MYSTERIOUS STRANGER
LIVING IN THE WOODS NEARBY AND
TALKED TO A LOCAL KNOWN FOR
COMMITTING SIMILAR STYLE
BREAK-INS.
BUT THOSE LEADS WENT NOWHERE, SO
DETECTIVES TURNED THEIR FOCUS IN
A NEW DIRECTION.
WAS IT POSSIBLE THE KILLER WAS
SOMEONE THEY HAD ALREADY MET?
HERE AGAIN IS DENNIS MURPHY.
>> Reporter: INVESTIGATORS IN
GROVETOWN, GEORGIA NOW HAD A
MURDER CASE ON THEIR HANDS.
KAY PARSONS HAD BEEN ASSAULTED
AND KILLED IN A HOME INVASION.
AND THE HOUSE OF HER GOOD FRIEND
BECKY NEXT DOOR HAD BEEN
RANSACKED TOO.
IS YOUR DOOR TO DOOR, YOUR
CANVASSING, COMING UP WITH
ANYTHING?
>> NO.
NOBODY -- NOBODY'S SEEN ANYBODY,
YOU KNOW, OUT OF THE ORDINARY IN
THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> Reporter: SO THEY TURNED TO
THE FIRST PERSON IN THE
NEIGHBORHOOD TO NOTICE SOMETHING
WAS WRONG -- THE CONTRACTOR
WHO'D ALERTED 911 -- FIRST MAN
ON THE SCENE.
INVESTIGATORS HAD TO WONDER WHY
HE WAS REALLY THERE.
>> AT THIS POINT -- EVERYBODY'S
A SUSPECT, YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW, AND LOGICALLY HE'S THE
FIRST ONE.
>> Reporter: EDMUNDS BROUGHT HIM
DOWN TO THE SUBSTATION FOR
QUESTIONING, AND THEY WENT
THROUGH THE STORY HE HAD TOLD AT
THE SCENE.
>> IT WAS AN -- AND I WALKED
DOWN TO THE HALL AND I SAID,
"HEY, IS ANYBODY IN THERE?"
AND -- ANYWAY -- I DIDN'T HEAR
NOTHIN'.
>> Reporter: BUT YOU ALSO HAVE
TO ASK HIM IF THAT'S REALLY WHAT
HAPPENED.
>> YES.
>> Reporter: I MEAN, HE'S THE
GUY WHO DISCOVERS THIS VIOLENT
CRIMINAL ACT, AND YOU WONDER IF
HE KNOWS MORE THAN HE'S SAYING.
>> OH, DEFINITELY.
>> Reporter: THEY PRESSED HIM TO
FIND OUT MORE ABOUT JUST WHAT
WORK HE WAS TO DO THERE, AND
WHETHER HE HAD WORKED FOR KAY
PARSONS BEFORE.
>> DID YOU HAVE THE KEY -- HAVE
THE DOOR OPEN TO THE HOUSE?
TO DO THE WORK?
>> WELL, WE -- WE -- WAS MOSTLY
OUTSIDE.
THE LONELIEST TIME THAT WE WAS
REALLY ON THE INSIDE IS WHEN SHE
CALLED ME UP AND SAID, I NEED A
LITTLE BIT FIXED ON THE INSIDE.
>> Reporter: YOU HAD THE BAD
LUCK OF BEIN' THE PERSON TO FIND
THIS.
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
>> Reporter: SO, THAT PUT YOU ON
THE LIST ALSO, MITCH, OF --
>> SURE.
SURE, YEAH --
>> Reporter: PEOPLE THEY WANNA
GET A FULL STORY FROM.
>> EXACTLY.
>> Reporter: MAYBE WITH SOME
SHARP QUESTIONS, HUH?
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.
I -- I KNEW BETTER TO WALK IN
THAT HOUSE, YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE I DID NOT WANT
ANYTHING -- MY FINGERPRINTS
ANYWHERE IN THAT HOUSE.
BECAUSE -- I JUST, YOU KNOW,
WATCHED ENOUGH TV TO KNOW
BETTER.
>> Reporter: WHAT'D YOU --
WHAT'D YOU SEE IN HIM IN TERMS
OF DEMEANOR?
>> HE SEEMED PRETTY GENUINE TO
ME.
HE WAS PRETTY SHAKEN UP.
>> Reporter: SO INVESTIGATORS
KNOCKED THE CONTRACTOR OFF THEIR
LIST BUT IN HIS INTERVIEW HE
HELPED POINT THEM TO SOMEONE
ELSE THAT BOY ON THE ROCK.
>> THEN I SEEN THAT BOY SITTIN'
THE NEXT-DOOR NEIGHBOR SITTIN'
DOWN ON A ROCK ACROSS THE
STREET.
AND -- THAT MADE ME KINDA
SUSPICIOUS RIGHT THERE, 'CAUSE I
BE -- I SAID -- I SAID, "I
WONDER IF THIS GUY'S A LOOKOUT."
RIGHT?
I MEAN, HE MIGHT BE STILL -- YOU
KNOW, SOMETHIN' IS GOIN' ON
HERE.
>> Reporter: MICHAEL, BECKY'S
22 YEAR OLD SON FROM NEXT DOOR.
REMEMBER, HE WAS ALSO ON THE
SCENE THAT MORNING WHEN DEPUTIES
ARRIVED.
A NEIGHBOR AND FAMILIAR FACE TO
KAY, THE VICTIM.
THAT GOT EDMUNDS THINKING.
>> I THOUGHT, YOU KNOW, IF SHE
CAME HOME AND SURPRISED THIS
BURGLAR AND SHE KNEW WHO THIS
BURGLAR WAS, HE COULDN'T LET HER
GET AWAY.
>> Reporter: YOU CAN ALMOST SEE
THAT LITTLE MOVIE PLAY OUT, THE
MOTIVATION, WHAT HAPPENED.
>> EXACTLY, EXACTLY.
SO WE STARTED LOOKIN' AT MICHAEL
PRETTY HARD.
>> Reporter: MICHAEL TOLD THEM
HE'D GOTTEN THERE AROUND
8;30 THAT MORNING ONLY TO FIND
HIS HOUSE HAD BEEN BURGLARIZED
AND HE'D PROMPTLY CALLED HIS
MOM.
BUT HE HADN'T CALLED THE POLICE,
WHICH SEEMED A BIT STRANGE TO
INVESTIGATORS.
WHAT'S MORE --
>> THERE WAS NO FORCED ENTRY TO
THAT RESIDENCE.
>> Reporter: THERE WASN'T?
>> THERE WAS NO FORCED ENTRY.
>> Reporter: THAT WAS ODD TOO,
AND THEY WERE ABOUT TO LEARN A
LOT MORE ABOUT MICHAEL.
HE WAS BECKY'S OLDEST SON.
HE AND HIS BROTHER CHRIS WERE
FROM A PRIOR MARRIAGE.
AND MICHAEL CAME WITH A HISTORY
OF TROUBLE, MOSTLY DRUGS.
SO, THAT'S GOTTA MAKE YOUR NOSE
TWITCH A LITTLE BIT.
>> MOST DEFINITELY.
HE'S ON THE SCENE WHEN WE GET
THERE.
HE'S HAD A LOTTA PROBLEMS IN THE
PAST WITH -- WITH -- WITH DRUGS.
SO THAT RAISED A LOTTA RED
FLAGS.
>> Reporter: OPPORTUNITY TO GET
QUICK CASH?
>> MOST DEFINITELY.
>> DRUG HABIT?
MAKE A BUY?
>> YOU KNOW, THEY GOTTA GET
MONEY.
AND THE BEST WAY TO DO THAT
IS -- IS BURGLARIES, YOU KNOW?
GET THE QUICK CASH.
>> Reporter: DID YOU HAVE
TROUBLE WITH DRUGS AT THE TIME?
>> I WON'T SAY TROUBLE, BUT IT
WAS --
>> Reporter: YOU WERE A REGULAR
CUSTOMER, HUH?
>> I MEAN, IT WAS A SOCIAL
THING.
WE'D BE -- BEING DUMB AND YOUNG,
THAT'S ALL.
>> Reporter: SMOKIN' WEED, OR
HARDER STUFF, MICHAEL?
>> AH, SMOKIN' WEED AND A LITTLE
HARDER STUFF, PILLS, THINGS LIKE
THAT.
>> Reporter: THIS IS METHADONE?
>> YEAH.
UH-HUH.
YES, SIR.
>> Reporter: WITH MICHAEL'S
PRESENCE ON THE SCENE, AND DRUGS
NOW IN THE EQUATION, EDMUNDS'
TEAM BROUGHT HIM DOWN TO THEIR
SUBSTATION FOR QUESTIONING.
>> NOW, I'M GONNA BE POINT-BLANK
WITH YA, IF YOU KNEW ANYTHING
ABOUT THIS YOU WOULD TELL ME
RIGHT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU
TOOK SOME METHADONE?
>> TODAY.
>> TODAY?
>> UH-HUH.
>> Reporter: SO MICHAEL HAD USED
METHADONE ON THE MORNING OF KAY
PARSONS' MURDER.
NOW INVESTIGATORS WANTED TO KNOW
MORE ABOUT WHERE EXACTLY HE WAS
WHEN THE ASSAULT HAPPENED.
MICHAEL SAID HIS MOM BECKY HAD
DROPPED HIM OFF AT A JOBSITE
JUST BEFORE 7AM TO DO SOME HOUSE
PAINTING.
>> WHEN DID YA TELL YOUR MOM YOU
HAD THIS PAINT JOB?
WHEN DID YOU TELL HER YOU
WERE --
>> TOLD HER A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
THIS MORNIN'.
>> Reporter: BUT HERE'S THE
THING.
HE DIDN'T DO ANY HOUSE PAINTING
THAT DAY.
AND HE INITIALLY LIED TO HIS MOM
AND INVESTIGATORS ABOUT WORKING.
>> AND THE WHOLE REASON YOU LIED
TO US WAS BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T
WANT YOUR MOM TO FIND OUT THAT
YOU DIDN'T REALLY HAVE A JOB?
>> YES, SIR.
>> THAT JUST THAT BLOWS MY MIND.
>> Reporter: AND THERE WAS
SOMETHING ELSE THAT REALLY
TROUBLED INVESTIGATORS.
IF MICHAEL WAS THE ATTACKER, HE
HAD CLEANED HIMSELF UP BEFORE
DEPUTIES GOT THERE.
HE HAD NO BLOOD ON HIS CLOTHES
OR VISIBLE WOUNDS.
BUT HE DID HAVE SOMETHING ELSE.
>> I ASKED HIM TO LET ME SEE THE
BOTTOM OF HIS SHOES.
AND AS HE LIFTED HIS SHOES UP, I
SAW SMALL PIECES OF GLASS STUCK
IN THE BOTTOM OF HIS TENNIS
SHOES.
AND THAT GLASS WAS THE SAME TYPE
OF GLASS FROM THE BACK DOOR AT
KAY PARSONS' HOUSE.
>> Reporter: IN THE
INTERROGATION ROOM MICHAEL
COULDN'T EXPLAIN HOW THE GLASS
FROM THE MURDER SCENE GOT THERE.
>> AS FAR AS GLASS THAT WAS
FOUND IN YOUR SHOES, HOW CAN YOU
EXPLAIN THAT?
>> GLASS IN MY SHOES?
>> UH-HUH.
>> I GUESS -- I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE -- I GUESS I DON'T KNOW.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
>> Reporter: SO, WHAT'S HE DOIN'
WITH THAT GLASS UNDER FOOT, HUH?
>> THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT I WANNA KNOW.
>> Reporter: INVESTIGATORS
TALKED TO MICHAEL'S BROTHER
CHRIS THE SON WHO'D ARRIVED AT
THE SCENE LATER WITH THEIR
MOTHER BECKY.
CHRIS SEEMED TO HAVE HIS LIFE
TOGETHER IN A WAY THAT MICHAEL
DIDN'T HE HAD A JOB EVEN HIS OWN
HOUSE.
THAT MORNING HE WAS HELPING HIS
MOM AT THE THERAPY CENTER WHERE
SHE WORKED.
>> YOUR MOM PICKS YOU UP ABOUT
WHAT TIME?
>> I GOT UP AT 7:00, BRUSHED MY
TEETH.
SHE -- SHE PULLED UP 7:10.
>> THEN YOU GO TO WORK WITH HER?
>> YES.
>> Reporter: THEN THEY ASKED HIM
ABOUT MICHAEL.
CHRIS SAID HE KNEW HIS BROTHER
TOOK DRUGS BUT HE SAID MICHAEL
WOULDN'T HAVE KILLED ANYONE.
>> DO YOU THINK YOUR BROTHER DID
THIS? OR DO YOU THINK SOMEBODY?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I DON'T THINK MY BROTHER HAS IT
IN HIS HEART.
>> I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT -- THAT -- THAT AT THIS
POINT, BROTHERLY LOVE IS NOT
OUTWEIGHIN' COMMON SENSE.
>> WELL --
>> BECAUSE I JUST SAW SOME STUFF
IN YOUR BROTHER JUST TALKIN' TO
HIM FOR ABOUT 20 MINUTES.
AND I'M SITTIN' THERE GOIN',
"WHAT?"
PEOPLE GET ON METHADONE.
THEY DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY.
AND THEY NOT WORKIN'.
>> WELL --
>> HOW THEY GONNA GET MONEY?
>> I -- I -- I AGREE ON THAT.
>> WELL, OUT OF EVERYBODY THAT
YOUR BROTHER HANGS AROUND
WITH --
>> WHO WOULD BE THE MOST LIKELY
TO DO SOMETHIN' --
>> YES, UH-HUH.
YEAH, YEAH.
>> LIKE THAT?
YOU MIGHT NEED TO GET A BIGGER
PIECE OF PAPER.
BECAUSE OF THOSE DRUGS, MAN.
>> I'D GO FOR SEVENTEEN HOURS.
>> Reporter: SO MICHAEL'S
BROTHER CONFIRMED THE TROUBLED
YOUNG MAN RAN WITH A SHADY
CROWD.
INVESTIGATORS WERE ALL EARS.
>> Reporter: DOES HIS
ASSOCIATION WITH THE HOUSE, HIS
BACK STORY, MAKE HIM A PERSON OF
INTEREST TO YOU?
>> HE'S DEFINITELY A PERSON OF
INTEREST.
>> Reporter: THE DEPUTIES KEPT
MICHAEL AT THE STATION FOR
NEARLY THREE HOURS BUT THEY
DIDN'T HOLD HIM THAT DAY.
HE GAVE THEM A NUMBER FOR HIS
ALIBI WITNESS THAT FRIEND HE'D
GONE TO SEE THAT MORNING.
WOULD HE VOUCH FOR MICHAEL?
>>> SOON ANOTHER MYSTERY IS
REVEALED AND ONCE AGAIN MICHAEL
JUMPS TO THE TOP OF THE
INVESTIGATORS' LIST.
COMING UP --
>> WE HAD SOME BLANK CHECKS IN
ONE OF OUR OFFICES THAT
DISAPPEARED.
>> IT WASN'T LOOKING REAL GOOD
FOR HIM.
THINGS STARTED PILING MUP SFWLCH
A AND NEW THEORY OF THE CRIME.
>> WE DIDN'T KNOW IF THEY WERE
IN THIS TOGETHER OR WHAT.
>> WHEN SECRETS ON HOT SPRINGS
DRIVE CONTINUES.
WHAT
>> WHEN SECRETS ON HOT SPRINGS
DRIVE CONTINUES.
Woman:
This is your wake-up call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis,
month after month,
the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
HUMIRA can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
HUMIRA targets and blocks
a source of inflammation
that contributes
to joint pain
and irreversible damage.
VO: HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections
including tuberculosis,
and cancers, including
lymphoma, have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Woman:
Help stop the clock
on further irreversible
joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here. Right now.
HUMIRA.
>> Reporter: SHERIFF'S DEPUTIES
WERE NOW ZEROING IN ON
MICHAEL BOWERS AS A PERSON OF
INTEREST IN THE MURDER OF
KAY PARSONS, HIS MOTHER'S BEST
FRIEND.
>> WITH THE GLASS IN HIS SHOE,
HIM BEING THE ONE SHOWING UP AT
THE HOUSE, FINDING THE BURGLARY
AND HIS PAST HISTORY OF DRUGS.
AND YOU KNOW, DRUGS AND
BURGLARIES GO HAND IN HAND.
>> Reporter: INVESTIGATORS
BELIEVED THAT KAY WAS BEATEN AT
HER HOME IN A NARROW WINDOW OF
TIME BETWEEN 7:10AM AND 7:20AM
THAT MORNING.
BUT MICHAEL SAID HE DIDN'T
ARRIVE AT THE SCENE UNTIL 8:30.
AND SAID HE HAD AN ALIBI FOR THE
TIME BEFORE THAT.
HE'D BEEN HANGING OUT, HE SAID,
WITH A FRIEND NAMED ANTHONY.
>> Reporter: WHAT'S THE STORY HE
TELLS YOU ABOUT THAT DAY?
>> WE PULL -- WE PULL ANTHONY IN
AND WE -- WE INTERVIEW HIM
AND -- AND ANTHONY'S, HE'S A
CHARACTER.
HE -- HE'S PRETTY LIVELY.
HE'S VERY TALKATIVE.
>> HE HADN'T HAD TIME TO TALK TO
MICHAEL.
WE KNEW MICHAEL HADN'T TALKED TO
HIM.
>> Reporter: SO YOU GOT TWO
UNVARNISHED STORIES, THIS MIGHT
WORK OUT. THEY HAVEN'T HAD A
CHANCE TO COMPARE NOTES.
>> EXACTLY.
>> WHAT TIME MICHAEL GET TO YOUR
HOUSE?
>> ROUGHLY.
>> YOU AWAKE, SLEEP, WHAT?
>> I WAS UP.
I WAS UP.
WELL, I WAS LAYING BACK DOWN.
I WAS LAID DOWN ON THE COUCH,
GETTING READY TO GO BACK TO
SLEEP.
I DIDN'T EXPECT HIM THAT EARLY.
BUT --
>> BUT YOU WERE EXPECTING HIM?
>> YEAH.
HE SAID HE WAS GONNA COME OVER.
>> HOW LONG WAS HE THERE?
>> TILL -- FROM WHEN HE GOT
THERE, WHICH WAS ROUGHLY
6:45 TILL 8:27 ON THE DOT.
>> THEY WERE PRETTY CONSISTENT.
YOU KNOW, ANTHONY WAS -- HIS --
HIS TIME WAS PRETTY CONSISTENT
WITH -- WITH MICHAEL'S.
BUT WE STILL, YOU KNOW, WE -- WE
DIDN'T KNOW IF THEY WERE IN THIS
TOGETHER OR -- OR WHAT.
>> ANGEL WAS ON.
THAT'S WHAT I WATCH IN THE
MORNING.
AND SOME --
>> YOU WATCH -- YOU WATCH THE
EPISODE OF ANGEL WEDNESDAY
MORNING?
THAT HOUR?
TELL ME WHAT YOU --
>> NO, ACTUALLY, I TALKED TO
MICHAEL FOR PRETTY MUCH THE
ENTIRE HOUR.
BUT ANGEL WAS ON THE BOOB TUBE.
>> Reporter: AS HE SAT IN THE
INTERVIEW ROOM, INVESTIGATORS
DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO MAKE OF THIS
TALKATIVE CHARACTER.
SO THEY HOOKED ANTHONY UP TO A
POLYGRAPH MACHINE.
AND ASKED HIM AGAIN WHERE HE AND
MICHAEL WERE THAT MORNING.
>> YOU DIDN'T EVEN COME CLOSE TO
PASSING THAT POLYGRAPH.
>> I'M SORRY.
BUT I'M NOT LYING ABOUT IT.
I TOLD HIM I'D TAKE ANOTHER ONE.
I MEAN I'M, IF I WAS LYING, WHY
THE HELL WOULD I HAVE SAID I'D
TAKE IT?
>> WELL, STRANGER THINGS HAVE
HAPPENED.
>> I'M SURE.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, I'M TELLING THE TRUTH.
SO IT IS WHAT IT IS.
I MEAN I -- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO
TELL YOU, SIR.
BUT YOU CAN -- I'LL GIVE YOU
WHATEVER YOU WANT, YOU KNOW,
BLOOD.
THEY ALREADY TOOK MY MOUTH,
SO --
>> YEAH.
>> BUT I DIDN'T DO ANY OF THIS,
MAN.
>> Reporter: ANTHONY REPEATED
OVER AND OVER THAT HE HAD
NOTHING TO DO WITH KAY PARSONS'
MURDER.
DIDN'T EVEN KNOW HER.
>> DUDE, I'M TRYING TO BE AS
STRAIGHT UP WITH YOU GUYS AS
POSSIBLE.
I MEAN --
>> WELL, AND THAT -- AND THAT'S
WHAT I WANT.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
>> YES, SIR.
I'M -- I'M NOT GONNA LIE ABOUT
IT.
I WANT YOU TO CATCH THE GUY.
I JUST -- I DON'T WANT YOU
LOOKING AT ME LIKE I DID THE
[ BLEEP ].
'CAUSE I AIN'T -- DUDE, I AIN'T
REAL COOL WITH YOU.
I DON'T THINK IT'S A REALLY --
YOU KNOW, IF YOU OR ME OR -- OR
SOME GUY GOT HURT, THAT'S ONE
THING.
YOU KNOW?
BUT NOT A LADY.
NOT SOMEBODY'S MOM.
>> Reporter: AND HE STARTED TO
PUT THE FINGER MORE ON MICHAEL.
>> HE KNOWS SOMETHING.
WELL, I DON'T BUT I DON'T
RIGHTLY KNOW.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT DOES HE KNOW?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT HE KNOWS.
DUDE, LOOK, YOU'RE NOT CATCHING
ME UP IN SOMETHING.
HE KNOWS SOMETHING.
>> WHAT DOES HE --
>> HE SAW SOMETHING, HE DID
SOMETHING, ONE OF THE ABOVE.
>> I WOULD ASSUME IF MICHAEL OR
ANY OF HIS PEOPLE HAD SUMPIN' TO
DO WITH IT IT'S FOR DOPE.
THEY'RE GONNA HAVE ENOUGH SENSE
TO [ BLEEP ] BE ABLE TO BEAT,
WHAT, AN ENTIRE TEAM OF
INVESTIGATORS?
I DOUBT IT, DUDE.
I DOUBT IT.
I FIGURE, BY THE TIME
EVERYBODY'S D.N.A. COMES BACK,
'CAUSE I KNOW I'M NOT THE ONLY
SWAB YOU GOT, SOMEBODY'LL GET
CAUGHT UP.
>> SO YOU -- YOU -- YOU'RE
COMPLETELY CONFIDENT YOUR D.N.A.
IS NOT IN THAT HOUSE ANYWHERE?
>> I KNOW IT'S NOT.
I KNOW IT'S NOT.
>> HE -- HE KEEPS SAYING, YOU
KNOW, "I -- I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING
SO I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO
WORRY ABOUT."
>> Reporter: BUT WAS HE IN FACT
ON YOUR LIST AT THAT POINT?
>> OH, HE -- HE WAS, YOU KNOW.
HE WAS, HE PUT HIMSELF WITH
MICHAEL.
>> WELL, I THINK YOU KNOW A
LITTLE BIT MORE THAN YOU'RE
TELLING ME.
>> SIR, I DON'T.
I -- I -- I'VE -- I'M GIVING YOU
PEARLS, MAN.
I'M GIVING YOU ALL I GOT.
I -- I'VE TOLD YOU GUYS
EVERYTHING I KNOW.
I KNOW THAT HE CAME OVER.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHEN HE LEFT.
I KNOW I WAS AT MY HOUSE.
THAT'S ALL I KNOW.
>> Reporter: FOR ALL HIS
QUESTIONS, INVESTIGATOR EDMUNDS
ULTIMATELY HAD NOTHING ON
ANTHONY.
A FAILED POLYGRAPH ISN'T
EVIDENCE, AND NOTHING CONNECTED
HIM TO THE CRIME.
BUT THEY WERE STILL LOOKING AT
MICHAEL, AND THERE WAS THE
INEVITABLE QUESTION OF MOTIVE.
SURE, MICHAEL WAS OPEN ABOUT HIS
DRUG USE, BUT THAT DIDN'T
ENTIRELY EXPLAIN WHY HE WOULD
SAVAGELY BEAT HIS MOM'S BEST
FRIEND.
>> MY BOOKKEEPER CAME TO ME AND
SAID "WE'VE GOT SOME ISSUES
HERE."
>> Reporter: JURGEN COWLING HAS
A STORY TO TELL ABOUT MICHAEL.
BECKY AND KAY BOTH WORKED FOR
HIM AT HEALING HANDS PHYSICAL
THERAPY CENTER, AND SOMETIMES
MICHAEL WOULD DO ODD JOBS AT THE
OFFICE TOO.
>> MICHAEL WOULD COME IN AND DO
SOME MORE, WE HAD SOME FLOORING
THAT'D BE PUT IN, SOME CARPET.
AND THEN HE WOULD COME IN AND
ASSIST.
>> Reporter: BUT AFTER A WHILE
PEOPLE IN THE OFFICE STARTED TO
NOTICE SOMETHING.
>> WE HAD SOME BLANK CHECKS
IN -- IN ONE OF OUR OFFICES THAT
DISAPPEARED.
>> Reporter: BECKY AND KAY'S
BOSS SAYS THE CHECKS WENT
MISSING WHILE MICHAEL HAD BEEN
DOING SOME CLEANING IN THE
OFFICE.
>> SO I -- I PULL -- BECKY IN.
SHE SAID SHE SAT DOWN WITH
MICHAEL AND TALKED ABOUT IT.
AND, OF COURSE, MICHAEL SAID,
"YES, IT WAS ME."
>> Reporter: HOW MUCH MONEY WAS
STOLEN IN THAT INCIDENT?
>> ABOUT 800 BUCKS.
>> Reporter: 800 BUCKS?
>> YEAH, THREE OR FOUR CHECKS,
ABOUT 800 BUCKS.
>> Reporter: AND IT WAS ALL
MICHAEL.
AND HE 'FESSED UP TO IT, HUH?
>> YES, SIR.
>> Reporter: SO BECKY MUST HAVE
BEEN, WHAT, EM -- EMBARRASSED?
>> YOU COULD TELL SHE WAS REALLY
DISTRAUGHT.
>> Reporter: THE HEALING HANDS
BOSS AGREED WITH BECKY THAT HE
WOULDN'T REPORT THE INCIDENT TO
POLICE, AS LONG AS MICHAEL NEVER
CAME BACK THERE.
BUT HAD BECKY'S FRIEND AND
CO-WORKER KAY FOUND OUT ABOUT
THE STOLEN CHECK FUNNY-BUSINESS?
COULD THAT HAVE LED TO A
CONFLICT BETWEEN MICHAEL AND
KAY?
BUT, HERE'S THE THING, THE
AUTHORITIES WOULDN'T EVEN LEARN
ABOUT THE "HEALING HANDS" THEFT
FOR MONTHS TO COME.
EVEN WITHOUT THAT STORY ABOUT
THE THEFT, MICHAEL WAS SHAPING
UP TO BE A PRIME SUSPECT IN THE
MURDER.
>> IT WASN'T LOOKING REAL GOOD
FOR HIM.
THINGS STARTED -- STARTED PILING
UP.
>> Reporter: THEN SOMETHING
HAPPENED THAT WOULD STAND THE
INVESTIGATION ON ITS HEAD MORE
VIOLENCE, MORE MAYHEM, WITH
ANOTHER SUDDEN ATTACK.
>>> COMING UP -- WHO WAS THE
VICTIM THIS TIME?
WAS SOMEONE STALKING WOMEN IN
THIS SMALL TOWN?
>> SOMEBODY CAME OUT OF THE
TREES AND HE SHOT ME.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHERE IT'S AT?
>> ON MY LEG.
>> WHEN SECRETS ON HOT SPRINGS
DRIVE CONTINUES.
LEG
>> WHEN SECRETS ON HOT SPRINGS
DRIVE CONTINUES.
WE DON'T FOLLOW THE NAYSAYERS.
♪ ♪ ♪
Guys go through a lot to
deal with shave irritation.
So, we built the
New Gillette SkinGuard
with a specialized guard
designed to reduce it.
Because we believe all men
deserve a razor just for them.
The best a man can get.
Gillette.
Discover.
Hi, what's this
Social Security Alert?
It's a free alert if
we find your Social
Security number on the dark web.
Good, cuz I'm a little
worried about
my information getting out.
Why's that?
[bird speaking]
My social is 8- 7- 5 dash
Okay, I see.
[bird laughing]
SOMEBODY thinks it's hilarious.
Free Social Security
Alerts from Discover.
♪ It is such a good time
to kiss ♪
to dance ♪
♪ It is such a good time to ♪
[ Laughing ]
♪ Scoobidoo doobidoo ♪
[ Goose honking ]
♪♪
[ Laughing ]
A bad day on the road still
beats a good one off it.
♪♪
Progressive helps keep you
out there.
♪♪
I'm a dancer,
casting directors will send me
a video of choreography.
I need my phone to work
while I'm on the subway.
You'll see me streaming a video,
trying not to fall.
(laughs)
(VO)
There when it matters.
Buy the new Galaxy S10
and get a Galaxy S10e on us.
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM SAYS
YOU CAN'T MAKE A
400 HORSEPOWER SEDAN,
THAT'S ALSO
ENVIRONMENTALLY CONSCIOUS.
WE DON'T FOLLOW
CONVENTIONAL WISDOM.
♪ ♪ ♪
Breathe freely fast, with Vicks
Sinex.
My congestion's gone.
I can breathe again! Ahhhh
I can breathe again! Ughh..
Vicks Sinex, Breathe On
>>> WELCOME BACK.
INVESTIGATORS HAD ZEROED IN ON
MICHAEL BOWERS AS THE PRIME
SUSPECT IN THE MURDER OF KAY
PARSONS.
MICHAEL'S MOM WAS KAY'S CLOSEST
FRIEND.
RAISING MORE QUESTIONS.
BUT SOON ANOTHER VIOLENT ATTACK
WOULD LEAD TO A STARTLING
ADMISSION.
HERE AGAIN IS DENNIS MURPHY.
>> BUT THERE WAS AT LEAST ONE
PERSON WHO STOOD SQUARELY
BEHIND.
BECKY'S GOOD FRIEND KNEW ALL
ABOUT MICHAEL'S STRUGGLE WITH
DRUGS.
STILL SHE WOULDN'T ACCEPT SHE
HAD ANYTHING TO DO WITH THE THE
MURDER.
>> DID YOU WONDER WHO WAS GOING
ON?
>> I DIDN'T REALLY.
KNOWING MICHAEL, I KNEW HE
WOULDN'T DO ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
>> Reporter: THEN JUST 36 HOURS
INTO THE MURDER INVESTIGATION
ANOTHER ATTACK. THIS TIME A
SHOOTING.
JUST TEN MILES FROM THE CRIME
SCENE ON HOT SPRINGS DRIVE.
>> 911 .
>> SOMEBODY CAME OUT FROM BEHIND
THE TREES AND HE SHOT ME.
>> Reporter: SERGEANT
STEVEN DOUGLAS WAS DISPATCHED TO
THE SCENE.
>> MY PARTNER AND I RECEIVED A
PHONE CALL FROM THE ROAD PATROL
DIVISION IN REFERENCE TO A WOMAN
WHO HAD APPARENTLY BEEN THE
VICTIM OF AN ARMED ROBBERY AS
SHE WAS LEAVING WORK THAT
EVENING.
AND HAD APPARENTLY BEEN SHOT IN
THE PROCESS.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHERE YOU'RE HIT
AT?
>> MY LEGS.
>> Reporter: THE LOCATION OF THE
SHOOTING SOUNDED FAMILIAR.
>> WHAT'S THE NAME OF YOUR
OFFICE?
>> IT'S HEALING HANDS PHYSICAL
THERAPY.
>> Reporter: SO DID THE NAME OF
THE VICTIM.
>> WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> BECKY SEARS.
>> Reporter: BECKY SEARS, THE
BEST FRIEND AND CO-WORKER OF
MURDER VICTIM KAY PARSONS.
>> THAT IS KIND OF A HOLY COW
MOMENT.
THIS IS THE SAME WOMAN NEXT DOOR
TO THIS HOUSE WHERE THERE'D BEEN
A VICIOUS BEATING.
>> YES.
IT SEEMED AN ODD SET OF
COINCIDENCES.
>> SO THIS IS THE BACK DOOR OF
HEALING HANDS?
>> THIS IS THE BACK DOOR OF THE
BUSINESS THAT WE GOT CALLED TO.
>> Reporter: AS THE SERGEANT
PULLED UP TO THE SCENE, HE
LEARNED BECKY HAD BEEN WORKING
LATE ON THE COMPANY PAYROLL.
SHE WAS HEADING TO HER CAR WHEN
SHE WAS JUMPED.
>> APPARENTLY WHEN SHE HAD
TURNED AROUND, AN UNKNOWN MALE
SUBJECT WEARING DARK CLOTHES AND
A WHITE BASEBALL CAP RUSHED OUT
OF THE BUSHES AT HER, WITH A
FIREARM, DEMANDING HIS MONEY OR
NEXT TIME IT WAS GOING TO BE HER
FACE.
>> Reporter: THAT'S WHEN THE
ASSAILANT SHOT BECKY IN THE
LEGS.
>> THE SUBJECT APPARENTLY DIDN'T
ROB HER, DIDN'T TAKE ANYTHING
FROM HER, BUT TURNED AROUND AND
RAN BACK INTO THE BUSHES THE WAY
THAT HE CAME.
>> SHE'S NOT KNOWN FOR DOING THE
NIGHT DEPOSITS WITH CASH.
THERE'S NO CASH HERE.
>> EXACTLY.
NOT AT THIS TIME OF NIGHT.
>> WHAT'S THE TARGET, WHAT ARE
YOU GOING TO GET?
HAS TO BE PERSONAL.
>> I WOULD THINK SO.
>> Reporter: EMTS TRANSPORTED
BECKY TO THE LOCAL HOSPITAL.
IT DIDN'T TAKE LONG FOR THE
TROUBLING NEWS TO REACH BECKY'S
FRIEND MICHELLE.
>> DID YOU TALK TO BECKY ON THE
PHONE AFTER SHE'D BEEN SHOT?
>> I DID.
I JUST ASKED HER, WAS SHE OK?
AND SHE SAID "I AM."
SHE SAID, "YOU KNOW, JUST TRYIN'
TO GET THRU THIS."
>> SHE'S YOUR FRIEND, YOU'RE
WORRIED, HUH?
>> YES, WORRIED ABOUT HER.
>> Reporter: SO WAS
TAMARA BALDWIN.
FIRST KAY NOW BECKY?
>> IT JUST, IT DID NOT MAKE
SENSE TO ME.
>> WHAT IN THE WORLD WAS GOIN'
ON?
>> THAT'S WHAT I WANTED TO KNOW.
>> Reporter: SHERIFF'S DEPUTIES
IMMEDIATELY CANVASSED THE
NEIGHBORHOOD, LOOKING FOR ANYONE
MATCHING BECKY'S DESCRIPTION OF
THE SHOOTER.
>> SO YOU HAVE A GUNMAN ON THE
GROUND ON THE LOOSE.
>> RIGHT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING ON THAT
SCORE?
>> WE HAD STARTED SENDING UNITS
OUT TO SEE IF ANYBODY HAD SEEN
ANYTHING, SEE IF ANYBODY HEARD
ANY GUNSHOTS.
SEE IF ANYBODY SAW ANYBODY
MATCHING THE DESCRIPTION OF THE
SUSPECT.
AND WE WERE NOT ABLE TO FIND
ANYTHING.
>> Reporter: THE ONLY FORENSIC
EVIDENCE DOUGLAS COULD FIND IN
THE PARKING LOT WAS
THE .25 CALIBER SLUG THAT GRAZED
BECKY'S LEGS.
>> HER SHOES WERE STILL LAYING
THERE.
>> WE FOUND A SPENT SHELL
CASING, AND THEN WE HAD ALSO
FOUND THE ACTUAL PROJECTILE
ITSELF, RIGHT ON THE EDGE OF THE
SIDEWALK.
>> AND YOU DIDN'T FIND A TOSSED
WEAPON IN THE VICINITY?
>> NO, NO WEAPONS.
>> Reporter: THE SHOOTER HAD
VANISHED WITHOUT A TRACE.
>> BUT YOU HAD MORE QUESTIONS,
DIDN'T YOU?
>> WE DID INDEED.
>> Reporter: BUT THOSE QUESTIONS
WOULD BE LEFT FOR JIMMY EDMUNDS,
WHOSE INVESTIGATION INTO
KAY PARSONS'S MURDER HAD
SUDDENLY BECOME A LOT MORE
COMPLEX.
>> HERE I'VE GOT TWO NEIGHBORS,
YOU KNOW, ONE HAS BEEN BEATEN TO
DEATH AND THE OTHER ONE HAS JUST
GOTTEN SHOT.
AND THEY BOTH WORKED AT HEALING
HANDS.
>> DO YOU BELIEVE THAT THE
GUNMAN WHO HAS WOUNDED BECKY IS
ALSO THE PERSON WHO'S BROKEN IN
AND FATALLY BEATEN MISS PARSONS?
>> OF COURSE THAT COMES TO MIND.
I MEAN, OF COURSE IT DOES.
IT'S JUST TOO MUCH OF A
COINCIDENCE.
>> Reporter: AND NOTHING ABOUT
THIS SHOOTING TOOK THE HEAT OFF
BECKY'S SON MICHAEL.
>> WHAT'S THE WORKING THEORY?
>> THE WORKING THEORY STILL IS,
MICHAEL'S STILL PRETTY HIGH UP
ON THE LIST.
SOMEBODY'S LOOKING FOR SOME
MONEY.
SOMEBODY OWES SOMEBODY SOME
>> Reporter: EDMUNDS HAD SOME
TOUGH, PERSONAL QUESTIONS FOR
BECKY ABOUT HER SON MICHAEL.
THANKFULLY THE WOUNDS TO BECKY'S
LEGS WERE SUPERFICIAL.
SO EDMUNDS GRABBED HIS NOTE PAD,
AND HIS TAPE RECORDER, AND
HEADED TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> BECKY, SHE'S IN THE HOSPITAL
BED.
>> RIGHT.
>> NOT TOO BADLY INJURED.
WHEN I'M TALKIN' TO HER, SHE'S,
YOU KNOW, SHE'S REALLY HURTING.
>> Reporter: THE INVESTIGATOR
THEN ASKED BECKY FOR DETAILS
ABOUT SHOOTING.
>> WHAT DID HE SAY TO YOU?
>> WHO?
>> THE GUY THAT SHOT YOU?
>> HE WANTED HIS MONEY OR NEXT
TIME IT WOULD BE MY FACE.
>> WHAT MONEY IS HE TALKING
ABOUT?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
WE DID NOT OWE ANYBODY ANY
MONEY.
>> DOES MICHAEL?
>> NOT THAT I KNOW OF.
>> I DON'T WANT YOU DEAD NEXT.
>> I DON'T THINK MICHAEL KNOWS.
UNLESS HE OWES MONEY FROM THE
PAST, I DON'T THINK HE OWES ANY
MONEY NOW.
>> Reporter: TO EDMUNDS, BECKY
SOUNDED LIKE A MOM UNWILLING OR
UNABLE TO WRAP HER HEAD AROUND
THE POSSIBILITY OF HER SON'S
INVOLVEMENT IN A MURDER.
>> I THINK HE'S TRYING TO STAY
AWAY FROM ALL OF THAT TO GET
OUT -- TO BETTER HIMSELF.
>> Reporter: EDMUNDS SPUN
THROUGH THE POSSIBILITIES --
WAS BECKY IN DENIAL?
WAS SHE COVERING UP FOR HER SON?
OR WAS HE HEADING DOWN THE WRONG
PATH WITH MICHAEL ALTOGETHER.
HE DECIDED TO CAST A WIDER NET.
>> IS THERE SOME -- ANY
RELATIONSHIPS YOU'RE NOT TELLING
US ABOUT?
>> LIKE?
>> YOU HAVEN'T HAD ANY PROBLEMS
WITH ANYBODY?
>> NO, NOBODY.
>> FAMILY PROBLEMS?
>> Reporter: THAT'S WHEN BECKY
REVEALED AN INTIMATE DETAIL FROM
HER RECENT PAST.
SHE AND HER HUSBAND TONY HAD
GONE THROUGH A ROUGH PATCH IN
THEIR MARRIAGE.
>> I MEAN MY HUSBAND AND I WERE
HAVING SOME PROBLEMS, WHICH WE
WERE THANKFULLY WORKING OUT.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY RELATIONSHIPS
ON THE SIDE?
>> I DID.
>> HOW LONG HAS THAT BEEN?
>> HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN OVER?
>> YEAH.
>> THREE MONTHS.
>> Reporter: SUDDENLY, ADDED TO
THE MIX OF A BRUTAL MURDER AND A
BIZARRE SHOOTING WAS THIS
ADMISSION OF AN EXTRA MARITAL
ROMANCE.
>> I MEAN IT WASN'T LIKE IT WAS
A LONG LASTING THING.
IT WAS JUST A COUPLE OF MONTHS
LONG.
>> Reporter: EDMUNDS DIDN'T
PRESS BECKY ANY FURTHER ABOUT
THE AFFAIR.
A HOSPITAL ROOM IMMEDIATELY
FOLLOWING A SHOOTING WAS NEITHER
THE TIME NOR THE PLACE.
BUT THE INVESTIGATOR WAS
INTRIGUED.
HE LEFT BECKY WONDERING WHO THE
"OTHER MAN" WAS.
>> I KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHIN'
THERE.
I JUST COULDN'T -- JUST COULDN'T
FIGURE OUT WHAT YET.
>> TURNED OUT THERE WAS?
>> THERE WAS.
YEAH, THERE WAS.
THERE WAS SOME SECRETS.
>> Reporter: COMING UP --
>> I NEVER MINUTE FOR THIS TO
HAPPEN.
HAPPEN
Let's be honest:
you need insurance.
But it's not really something
you want to buy.
It's not sexy.
Or delicious.
Or fun.
But since you need both car
and home insurance,
why not bundle them with
Esurance and save up to 10%?
Which you can spend on things
you really want to buy, like...
well, I don't know what
you'd wanna buy
because I'm just
a guy on your TV.
Esurance. It's surprisingly
painless.