PEOPLE.
>> WE'LL HAVE THIS CONVERSATION
MANY TIMES IN THE WEEKS TO COME.
OTHERWISE, HAVE A HAPPY FOURTH.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
>> RIGHT BACK AT YA.
>> READ THE DECLARATION OF
INDEPENDENCE.
REMEMBER WHAT THE FOURTH OF JULY
IS ABOUT AND THE VALUES WE WANT
TO UPHOLD.
>> I THINK THE SAME THING.
WE SHOULD NOT BE POLITICIZING
TOMORROW, FOURTH OF JULY.
IT'S A DAY OF INDEPENDENCE, IT'S
A DAY OF KNOWING WHO WE ARE AND
REMEMBERING WHO WE ARE.
>> WE CELEBRATE THE FOURTH OF
JULY IN THE MIDST OF A SERIOUS
MORAL CRISIS.
WHERE WILL WE BE, WHO ARE WE?
>> THE PRESIDENT SAID THERE WILL
BE THE, QUOTE, SHOW OF A
LIFETIME IN WASHINGTON.
CHRIS JANSEN PICKS UP THE SHOW
RIGHT NOW.
>> GOOD MORNING.
I'M CHRIS JANSEN IN FOR ALEX
WITT.
PHOTOS THAT SHOW SQUALID
CONDITIONS AT MIGRANT CENTERS
AND IT'S EVEN MORE WIDESPREAD
THAN WE KNEW.
THESE SERIOUS AND DANGEROUS
SITUATIONS DETAILED FROM OUR OWN
INSPECTOR GENERAL AFTER SURPRISE
VISITS TO MULTIPLE FACILITIES.
THOSE PHOTOS REVEALED NO HOT
MEALS, NO ABILITY TO SHOWER.
ADULTS GIVEN ONLY BOLOGNA
SANDWICHES TO EAT, CAUSING
HEALTH PROBLEMS.
WHEN DETECTIVES SAW THEM, THEY
BANGED ON WINDOWS AND HELD UP
SIGNS, DESPERATE FOR RELEASE.
ONE OF THE SIGNS SAID, HELP, 40
DAYS HERE.
THAT WOULD VIOLATE A FEDERAL
COURT ORDER THAT MIGRANTS BE
HELD NO LONGER THAN 72 HOURS.
A SENIOR MANAGER DESCRIBED THE
WHOLE SITUATION AS, QUOTE, A
TICKING TIME BOMB.
OUR OWN JACOB SOBOROFF HAS SEEN
SOME OF THESE BORDER FACILITIES
WITH HIS OWN EYES, BUT WOW, THIS
REPORT, EVEN THOUGH WE KNEW SO
MUCH, IT WAS SHOCKING TO SEE IT
ALL THERE IN ONE PLACE.
YOUR REACTION TO THIS NEW REPORT
WHICH CITES IMMEDIATE HEALTH AND
SAFETY CONCERNS NOT AT ONE, OR
TWO, BUT SEVEN DIFFERENT SITES.
>> YOU JUST READ WHAT I BELIEVE
TO BE THE KEY PHRASE, THAT THIS
THING IS A TICKING TIME BOMB.
THIS IS NOT JUST A PHRASE THAT
CAN BE USED TO DESCRIBE THE
CONDITIONS IN THOSE SEVEN
FACILITIES IN THE RIO GRANDLY
VALLEY.
THE FACILITY I'VE BEEN INSIDE,
THAT CENTRAL PROCESSING STATION
THERE IN THE RIO GRANDE VALLEY
WHERE THEY SEPARATED MORE KIDS
THAN ANYWHERE ELSE ALONG THE
SOUTHERN BORDER, THE TICKING
TIME BOMB CAN BE USED TO
DESCRIBE THE WAY THE BORDER HAS
BEEN DETAINING MIGRANTS FOR
DECADES.
THESE ARE PRISONS, JAILS.
THEY TREAT MIGRANTS AS IF THEY
ARE PRISONERS, AS IF THEY ARE
CRIMINALS COMING INTO THIS
COUNTRY.
THEY'VE ALWAYS BEEN SET UP AS
INTAKE/JAIL PROCESSING TYPE
STATIONS WHERE NO ONE IS
SUPPOSED TO BE THERE LONGER THAN
72 HOURS, AND IT WAS ONLY A
MATTER OF TIME BEFORE THEY WOULD
SEE A SURGE LIKE THEY DID AND
LIKE THEY ARE CIEGA LONG THE
SOUTHERN BORDER TODAY.
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU HAVE TENS
OF THOUSANDS, HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE COMING INTO
THE COUNTRY AND ARE BEING PLACED
INTO TINY JAIL-LIKE FACILITIES
THAT ARE DESIGNED FOR SINGLE
ADULT MALES TO BE THERE DURING A
BRIEF PERIOD OF TIME.
IT'S EXACTLY WHAT WE'RE SEEING
IN THIS DHS REPORT ABOUT THE RMV
SECTOR, AND IT'S WHAT'S BEEN
GOING ON IN EL PASO JUST A
COUPLE WEEKS AGO.
>> AND A WEEK AGO WAS WHEN THIS
INSPECTION WAS DONE, AND THE DHS
SAID IT REQUIRED IMMEDIATE
ATTENTION AND ACTION, SO IT
SOUNDS LIKE, AT LEAST IN SOME
INSTANCES, THERE ARE NO MAJOR
CHANGES IN THE LAST COUPLE
WEEKS.
IS THAT YOUR READ?
>> THE CONDITIONS ARE NOT GOING
TO GET BETTER QUICKLY IN THESE
FACILITIES WHEN IT COMES TO THE
FACILITIES THEMSELVES AND THE
INFRASTRUCTURE THAT'S DOWN
THERE.
THAT'S THE CONVERSATION GOING ON
RIGHT NOW, PARTICULARLY AMONG
THE DEMOCRATS.
WHAT DO YOU DO ABOUT THE WAY
THIS COUNTRY IS HOLDING MIGRANTS
WHEN THEY COME INTO THIS
COUNTRY?
BUT I WILL SAY IF THERE IS ANY
BRIGHT SPOT IN ALL OF THIS, JUST
A COUPLE MONTHS AGO THERE WERE
OVER 2300 -- JULIA AINSLEY
REPORTED THIS YESTERDAY -- 2300
CHILDREN IN BORDER PROTECTION IN
FACILITIES JUST LIKE THIS.
AS OF YESTERDAY THERE WAS ONLY A
COUPLE OF HUNDRED AND THEY'VE
BEEN MOVED TO FACILITIES THAT
ARE OPERATED BY HHS IN OTHER
AREAS, NOT JUST AT THE SOUTHWEST
BORDER BUT ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
IT DOESN'T MEAN THAT THE
FACILITIES ARE GETTING ANY
BETTER, IT MEANS THAT THE
CHILDREN FOR NOW HAVE BEEN MOVED
OUT IN LARGE PART, AT LEAST
ACCORDING TO WHAT JULIA HAS
LEARNED FROM CDP.
>> I THOUGHT AT ONE POINT A BABY
WAS BEING HELD IN A PLACE THAT
WAS REALLY COLD, AND ACTUALLY
THEIR HANDS AND FEET HAD TURNED
BLUE.
OBVIOUSLY THERE ARE SERIOUS
PROBLEMS HERE.
JAKE, IF YOU'RE GOING TO STAY
WITH ME, I WANT TO BRING IN
BUREAU CHIEF PHIL RUCKER, AND
FOUNDER OF STRATEGIES, AND SKD
KNICKERBOCKER.
SO PHIL, WE SEE THE
ADMINISTRATION CITING THESE
ISSUES.
IS THERE ANY CHANGE HERE AT ALL?
>> NO.
RATHER THERE IS A FOCUS ON THE
NUMBERS, HOW MANY PEOPLE ARE
CROSSING THE BORDER, HOW MANY
PEOPLE ARE BEING DETAINED.
WE'RE HEARING FROM OFFICIALS IN
THE ADMINISTRATION THAT THOSE
NUMBERS HAVE BEEN DECLINING IN
RECENT WEEKS FROM A HIGH IN MAY,
BUT WE'VE NOT SEEN THE PRESIDENT
REALLY FORCEFULLY TAKE CONTROL
OF THIS ISSUE AND TALK ABOUT THE
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS THAT WE SEE
PLAYING OUT THAT'S SO WELL
DOCUMENTED IN THAT IG REPORT AND
IN THE REPORTING FROM PEOPLE
LIKE JACOB.
>> AND IT'S A HUMANITARIAN
CRISIS, RICK, THAT IS UNFOLDING
IN THE MIDDLE OF AN ELECTION
SEASON.
BUT EVEN DHS RESPONDED TO THIS
REPORT BY SAYING CONGRESS'
FAILURE TO ACT IS INCENTIVIING
ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION.
BUT DO YOU BELIEVE ANYTHING WILL
CHANGE BEFORE THE ELECTION, OR
HAS THIS ISSUE JUST BECOME TOO
POLITICIZED?
>> I WOULD LIKE TO STEP BACK AND
PUT IT IN CONTEXT.
THIS HAS OCCURRED OVER DECADES
OF TIME, AND BOTH PARTIES ARE TO
BLAME, AND I REALIZE THE
REPUBLICAN ADMINISTRATION IS IN
CHARGE NOW.
BUT, LOOK, I AGREE WITH CHAIRMAN
NADLER THAT SOMEONE NEEDS TO BE
HELD ACCOUNTABLE.
YES, WE NEED TO WEED OUT THE BAD
APPLES, BUT I'M GOING TO BE VERY
CAREFUL ABOUT DEMONIZING THE
BORDER PATROL.
THE PROBLEM IS THESE FACILITIES
THAT THE BORDER PATROL IS
WORKING ARE NOT DESIGNED TO HOLD
FAMILIES AND A NUMBER OF PEOPLE,
AND ESPECIALLY CHILDREN, FOR THE
TIME THEY'RE DOING IT.
SO I HAVE TO SAY THE BOTTOM LINE
IS IF WE ARE ILL-EQUIPPED TO
TREAT IMMIGRANTS HUMANELY, THEN
I WOULD BE FOR --
>> IT'S NOT IF.
THEY'RE NOT BEING TREATED
HUMANELY.
THEY'RE BEING TOLD TO DRINK OUT
OF TOILETS, KIDS ARE FREEZING.
>> HERE'S WHAT I WOULD SAY.
IF I WERE A MEMBER OF CONGRESS,
I WOULD BE SAYING, WE NEED TO
RELEASE THE MAJORITY OF THESE
PEOPLE TODAY.
MAYBE PEOPLE WHO WERE KNOWN TO
BE DANGEROUS WOULD STAY IN
DETENTION, BUT THE MAJORITY OF
THESE PEOPLE NEED TO BE RELEASED
TODAY BECAUSE WE CANNOT TOLERATE
A COUNTRY THAT WE ARE TREATING
PEOPLE SO INHUMANELY.
>> WELL, I MEAN, WE HAVE 11
DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES FOR
PRESIDENT THAT ARE MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS, BUT THAT IGNORES THE
FACT THAT ULTIMATELY THE BUCK
STOPS WITH THE PRESIDENT, AND IT
IS THE PRESIDENT WHO PUT
POLICIES IN PLACE THAT LED US TO
WHERE WE ARE RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH, THIS REPORT IS
ALARMING, IT'S SHOCKING.
A LOT OF THE IMAGES WE'VE SEEN
ARE ALARMING AND SHOCKING.
I THINK IT JUST HIGHLIGHTS HOW
BIG OF A FAILURE THIS WHITE
HOUSE'S IMMIGRATION POLICY IS.
FROM TOP TO BOTTOM, IT'S NOT
KEEPING US SAFER AND IT'S
INHUMANE.
I THINK WHAT WE'RE GOING TO SEE
FROM DEMOCRATS OVER THE NEXT FEW
WEEKS, I THINK THERE IS GOING TO
BE A HEARING NEXT WEEK IN THE
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE WHERE THE
CDP WILL COME AND TESTIFY.
DEMOCRATS HAVE ALSO REQUESTED
HUNDREDS, IF NOT THOUSANDS AND
THOUSANDS OF DOCUMENTS FROM THIS
ADMINISTRATION ON THEIR
IMMIGRATION POLICIES.
AND THEY'VE BEEN MET WITH NO.
THE ADMINISTRATION HAS REFUSED
TO TURN OVER THIS PAPERWORK.
WHEN THE ADMINISTRATION BLAMES
CONGRESS, THEY'RE NOT
COOPERATING WITH CONGRESS SO
CONGRESS CAN HELP SOLVE THIS
ISSUE WITH THIS ADMINISTRATION.
SO THE BUCK DEFINITELY STOPS
WITH TRUMP AND THEY'RE
DEFINITELY DOING EVERYTHING THEY
CAN TO STONEWALL HERE.
>> WE JUST GOT FROM TWITTER FROM
THE ACTIVE INVESTIGATOR THAT
HE'S POSTED BORDERED PATROL
PERSONNEL.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THAT?
>> TO HEAR ABOUT THAT FROM KEVIN
McALEENAN IS GOOD, BUT REMEMBER,
HE CALLED THESE CONDITIONS
UNSUBSTANTIATED AS EARLY AS LAST
FRIDAY.
WHEN YOU HEAR A CULTURE OF 9500
BORDER PATROL AGENTS IN A SECRET
FACEBOOK GROUP, THIS WAS FROM
PRO PUBLICA TALKING, IN THE WAY
THAT THEY WERE, IT'S HARD NOT TO
GIVE CREDENCE OF THE ALLEGATIONS
WE HEAR COMING OUT OF THESE
FACILITIES.
WE'VE HEARD THE REPORTS FROM THE
DEMOCRATIC LAWMAKERS WHO WERE
DOWN THERE EARLIER THIS WEEK.
I'VE SEEN CERTAIN CONDITIONS
DOWN THERE WITH MY OWN EYES.
AND, AGAIN, IT'S A POSITIVE
STEP, I SUPPOSE, BUT IT'S
CERTAINLY NOT GOING TO ALLEVIATE
WHAT IS HAPPENING, AS RICK SAID,
RIGHT NOW DOWN THERE.
>> AND WE JUST GOT A REPORT, I
GUESS, IN THE LAST 24 HOURS OR
SO, JACOB, THAT A YOUNG GIRL OR
A TWO-YEAR-OLD APPARENTLY
DROWNED IN THE RIO GRANDE AFTER
WE SAW THAT HEARTBREAKING
PICTURE OF A FATHER AND HIS
CHILD.
>> YEAH.
AGAIN, THIS IS ANOTHER HORRIFIC
STORY OF A FAMILY WHO JUST
WANTED TO ESCAPE THEIR LIVES
WHERE THEY WERE TO COME FOR A
BETTER LIFE.
THIS REPORTEDLY WAS A HAITIAN
NATIONAL WITH A CHILD WHO WAS A
BRAZILIAN NATIONAL CROSSING THE
RIO GRANDE.
THEY WERE SEPARATED IN THE RIVER
AND A SEARCH IS ONGOING RIGHT
NOW BY THE BORDER PATROL.
IF IT TURNS OUT THIS CHILD DID
NOT SURVIVE, I WANT EVERYBODY TO
REMEMBER THAT 7,000 PEOPLE HAVE
DIED TRYING TO COME INTO THIS
COUNTRY SINCE 1998.
THE FAILURES OF OUR BORDER
POLICY AS AMERICANS HAVE BEEN
SYSTEMIC LITERALLY FOR DECADES
IN DEMOCRATIC AND REPUBLICAN
ADMINISTRATIONS.
NOBODY HAS TREATED MIGRANTS MORE
INHUMANELY THAN THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION, BUT THIS IS A
PROBLEM THAT HAS BEEN FESTERING
LITERALLY FOR DECADES, AND NOW
FINALLY, AS FAR AS I'M
CONCERNED, IT'S REFRESHING, IT'S
REASSURING TO HEAR ALL OF US
DEBATING HOW WE FIX IT SO THIS
DOES NOT CONTINUE TO HAPPEN.
>> WELL, IT DEPENDS ON WHO THE
"WE" IS BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT IS
ACTUALLY DOUBLING DOWN.
YOU HAVE CHILDREN WHO ARE DYING,
REPORTS OF ADULTS THAT ARE
LITERALLY IN CELLS THAT ARE SO
TIGHTLY PACKED THAT THEY CAN'T
SIT DOWN.
STANDING ROOM ONLY FOR A WEEK AT
A TIME.
AND YET HE'S SIGNALLING MORE
DETENTIONS AFTER TOMORROW,
IMPOSING FINES ON UNDOCUMENTED
MIGRANTS WHO DON'T SHOW UP FOR
COURT.
PHIL, I WAS THINKING BACK TO
WHEN THE FIRST LADY WENT DOWN AT
THE TIME OF THE FAMILY
SEPARATION AND SOME PEOPLE
THOUGHT, WELL, MAYBE THE FIRST
LADY AND IVANKA WILL IMPRESS
UPON HIM THE INHUMANITY OF
WHAT'S HAPPENING DOWN THERE.
BUT IS THERE ANY SCENARIO THAT
YOU SEE HAVING COVERED THIS
PRESIDENT THAT SUGGESTS TO YOU
THAT HE WILL SHY AWAY FROM THIS
AS A CAMPAIGN ISSUE?
>> NOT AT ALL, CHRIS.
THIS IS AN ISSUE THAT THE
PRESIDENT BELIEVES IS A WINNING
ISSUE FOR HIM.
POLITICALLY HE BELIEVES HIS
TOUGH STANCE ON IMMIGRATION IS
WHAT GOT HIM THE PRESIDENCY IN
THE FIRST PLACE, IT'S WHAT
HELPED HIM DEFEAT ALL THOSE
REPUBLICAN CHALLENGERS IN THE
2016 PRIMARIES, AND HE BELIEVES
IT'S WHAT'S GOING TO WIN HIM
REELECTION.
IT'S WHY YOU HEAR HIM TALK ABOUT
IT AT EVERY SINGLE RALLY.
AND HIS ADVISERS SAY THEY HOPE
THIS ISSUE STAYS IN THE
HEADLINES FOR EVERY DAY BETWEEN
NOW AND ELECTION DAY, AND SO THE
FIRST LADY CAN TRY TO PUT A
SPOTLIGHT ON THE HUMANITARIAN
ISSUE, ALTHOUGH WE'VE NOT SEEN
OR HEARD ANYTHING FROM HER IN
THE LAST FEW WEEKS HERE, AND
IVANKA TRUMP CAN TALK ABOUT WHAT
SHE WANTS TO TALK ABOUT, BUT THE
PRESIDENT BELIEVES THIS IS HOW
HE WINS REELECTION.
>> JACOB SOBOROFF, THANK YOU SO
MUCH FOR YOUR CONTINUED
REPORTING.
EVERYONE ELSE, YOU'RE COMING
BACK, SO I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
>>> COMING UP, IT'S AN ALL-OUT
IOWA BLITZ.
SEVEN DEMOCRATS CAMPAIGNING
TODAY ACROSS THE STATE.
DETAILS ON BERNIE SANDERS'
STRATEGY, SOME BRAND NEW FUND
NUMBERS AND SOME NEW POLL
NUMBERS.
>>> AS THE TANKS ROLL INTO D.C.
FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP'S COLOSSAL
FOURTH OF JULY CELEBRATION, WE
GET A LOOK AT HOW MUCH THE
EXTRAVAGANZA IS GOING TO COST
YOU, THE TAXPAYERS.
T
YOU, THE TAXPAYERS
♪♪
And with Bank of America
and Merrill,
the benefits you get
can grow, too.
As a Preferred Rewards member,
you can enjoy priority service
and exclusive discounts...
so your growing life
can be more rewarding, too.
♪♪
What would you like
the power to do?
♪♪
Make fitness routine
with Pure Protein.
High protein.
Low sugar.
Tastes great!
High protein.
Low sugar.
So good!
High protein.
Low sugar.
Mmmm,
Birthday cake!
Pure Protein.
The best combination for
every fitness routine.
Let's get down to business.
The business of family time...
...and downtime.
...and you time.
...and forgetting what time it
is...altogether.
Modernized Comfort Inns
and Suites have been refreshed
because when your business
is making time,
our business is you.
Get the lowest price guaranteed
on all Choice hotels
when you book direct at
ChoiceHotels.com.
Brushing only reaches
25% of your mouth.
LISTERINE® cleans
virtually 100%.
Helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%.
Always go for 100.
Bring Out the Bold™
(Gasp)
(Singsong)
Budget meeting!
Sweet.
If you compare last quarter
to this quarter...
Various: Mmm.
It's no wonder everything
seems a little better
with the creamy taste
of Philly,
made with fresh milk
and real cream.
You're turning onto the
street
when you barely
clip a passing car.te
of Philly,
Minor accident
—no big deal, right?
Wrong. Your insurance
company is gonna raise
your rate after the other
car got a scratch so small
you coulda fixed
it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that
pen and use it to sign up
with a different
insurance company.
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because of
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>>> WE'RE NOW EXACTLY SEVEN
MONTHS AWAY FROM THE IOWA
CAUCUS, AS DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES
ARE AWARE.
SEVEN OF THE CANDIDATES ARE
BARNSTORMING THE STATE TODAY
WHILE THE LATEST IOWA POLLS ARE
RELEASED.
KAMALA HARRIS IS SURGING IN
IOWA, JUMPING INTO SECOND AND
CLOSING IN ON FRONTRUNNER JOE
BIDEN.
ELIZABETH WARREN ALSO GOT A
POST-DATE BUMP WHILE PETE
BUTTIGIEG IS THERE.
JOE BIDEN IS DROPPING NOT JUST
IN IOWA BUT NATIONALLY.
IS THERE ANY INDICATION THAT HIS
CAMPAIGN IS SWITCHING STRATEGY?
>> THE STRATEGY WAS SLOWLY
BUILDING THIS CAMPAIGN FROM THE
GROUND UP, AND OF COURSE HIS
TEAM IS POINT TO GO AN ABC POLL
THAT SHOWS HIS SUPPORT ACTUALLY
INCREASING, TICKING UP JUST A
FEW POINTS.
HIS CAMPAIGN MANAGER HAD A VIDEO
BRIEFING FOR SUPPORTERS LAST
NIGHT, AND IN THAT BRIEFING HE
SAID THERE WILL BE PEAKS AND
VALLEYS BUT THEY'RE GOING TO
STAY THE COURSE.
IF YOU LOOK AT THIS TRIP TO IOWA
THAT SENATOR SANDERS IS DOING,
YOU NOTICE A COUPLE SUBTLE
SHIFTS IN HIS STRATEGY.
NUMBER ONE, HIS FOCUS ON RETAIL
POLITICS.
THERE WILL NOT BE AS MANY
TRADITIONAL RALLIES THAT HE HAS.
HE'S HAVING ICE CREAM SOCIALS,
THOUGH.
AS YOU SAW LAST NIGHT, HE STILL
GIVES LONG SPEECHES AT THESE ICE
CREAM SOCIALS BUT HE'S TRYING TO
MAKE PARADES AND SHAKE HANDS ON
THIS HOLIDAY.
THEY ARE OPENING THREE NEW
OFFICES IN THE STATE OF IOWA.
THEY'RE ALSO HIGHLIGHTING THEIR
VOLUNTEER FORCE.
THEY'RE SHOWING THEY HAVE THIS
40s THAT CAN DELIVER HIM TO
VICTORY COME FEBRUARY 3rd AND
COME THAT CAUCUS TIME.
THEY'RE FOCUSED NOT ONLY ON
THOSE RALLIES BUT ALSO
ACTIVATING THE SUPPORTERS AND
GETTING THEM OUT THERE AS MANY
CANDIDATES ARE HERE AND FOCUSED
ON GETTING THOSE IOWA VOTERS.
>> THE DEBATE HAS CATAPULTED
KAMALA HARRIS WHO YOU'RE WITH IN
SERIOUS CONTENTION.
BUT WE ALSO KNOW DEBATE BOUNCES
CAN BE SHORT-LIVED.
HAVE YOU SEEN ANY ADJUSTMENTS ON
HER CAMPAIGN TO CAPITALIZE ON
THIS, AND I ALSO WANT TO KNOW
ABOUT HER FUNDRAISING BECAUSE WE
KNOW SHE MADE $2 MILLION IN 24
HOURS BUT WE HAVEN'T SEEN HER
QUARTERLY NUMBERS.
>> Reporter: YEAH, WE HAVEN'T
SEEN THE QUARTERLY NUMBERS YET.
THEY EXPECT TO RELEASE THOSE IN
THE NEXT COUPLE DAYS.
AFTER HER PERFORMANCE THE
CAMPAIGN RAISED $3 MILLION JUST
IN ONLINE DONATIONS.
SHE HAD MULTIPLE FUNDRAISING
EVENTS IN CALIFORNIA WHERE SHE
RAISED AN ADDITIONAL $6 MILLION,
THE CAMPAIGN TELLS US.
WHAT IS THE CONDITION OF THIS
CAMPAIGN RIGHT NOW COMING OUT OF
THE DEBATE?
THE REALITY RIGHT HERE IN IOWA
IS THEY NOW HAVE 65 PAID
STAFFERS HERE ON THE GROUND IN
IOWA.
THEY LOOKED AT THAT DEBATE AS AN
OPPORTUNITY -- AS BEING MORE
THAN A DEBATE BUMP.
THEY BELIEVE THIS SUMMER IS THAT
MOMENT WHEN PEOPLE WOULD START
PAYING ATTENTION.
WE ARE AS OF NOW SEVEN DAYS AWAY
FROM THAT IOWA CAUCUS.
I ASKED KAMALA HARRIS, I WAS
WITH HER IN CALIFORNIA OVER THE
WEEKEND.
I ASKED HER ON SUNDAY HOW SHE
LOOKED AT APPROACHING THIS
CAMPAIGN GOING FORWARD AND
WHETHER SHE WAS GOING TO TAKE AN
APPROACH OF PROSECUTING THE CASE
AGAINST HER DEMOCRATIC
OPPONENTS.
SHE WAIVERED WITHOUT ANSWERING
DIRECTLY, AND I ASKED HER, WOULD
YOU ASK FOR COMMENT FROM YOUR
DEMOCRATIC OPPONENTS.
SHE WOULD NOT ANSWER THAT
QUESTION, BUT SHE'LL BE HERE
OVER THE NEXT THREE DAYS.
>> GARRETT, A NUMBER OF OTHER
CANDIDATES ARE THERE TODAY.
MONEY AND POLLS, TWO BIG THINGS.
I DO ALWAYS FIND IT INTERESTING
WHEN THE DEADLINE COMES, SOME
CANDIDATES, USUALLY THE ONES
THAT HAD A GREAT QUARTER, GET
OUT THERE AHEAD OF EVERYTHING
AND THE REST LAG BEHIND.
ANY SUGGESTION ON WHEN WE'LL SEE
SOME OF THESE OTHER NUMBERS AND
WHAT ARE THEY WAITING FOR?
BETO O'ROURKE SEEMED TO SUGGEST
YESTERDAY HE HAD NO IDEA HOW
MUCH MONEY HE HAD RAISED IN THAT
LAST QUARTER.
>> Reporter: YEAH, I DON'T BUY
THAT FOR ONE SECOND, CHRIS.
I'M SURE THAT HE MAY NOT KNOW
THE EXACT TOTAL, BUT THESE
CAMPAIGNS WATCH THEIR
FUNDRAISING NUMBERS PROBABLY
CLOSER THAN THEY WATCH THEIR
POLLING NUMBERS.
THE CANDIDATE WOULD KNOW WHETHER
OR NOT THEY'RE ON TRACK TO HIT
THEIR QUARTERLY GOALS OR NOT, AT
THE VERY LEAST.
A LOT OF THIS IS NEW CYCLE
MANAGEMENT.
O'ROURKE, YOU'LL REMEMBER IN THE
FIRST QUARTER, HIS CAMPAIGN
WAITED AND HELD THE NUMBERS OVER
THE WEEKEND.
I THINK IT WAS A TERRORIST
ATTACK THAT HAPPENED ON A
THURSDAY OR FRIDAY OR SOMETHING
OF THAT NATURE.
THEY DECIDED NOT TO RELEASE THEM
BECAUSE THEY DIDN'T WANT IT TO
GET CAUGHT UP IN THE WASH OR
LOOK LIKE THEY WERE BRAGGING.
IF YOU'RE SOMEONE WHO WANTS TO
BRAG ABOUT YOUR FUNDRAISING
NUMBERS, TODAY IS THE LAST DAY
TO DO THAT FOR A WHILE.
IF YOU'RE CAUGHT UP IN THIS
HOLIDAY WEEKEND, AND FOR SOMEONE
WHO WANTS TO BURY THEIR NUMBERS,
THEY'RE DISAPPOINTING, NOT WHAT
YOU WANTED THEM TO BE, GREAT
TIME TO NOT RELEASE YOUR
NUMBERS.
O'ROURKE IS HERE, BIDEN IS HERE,
KLOBUCHAR IS HERE.
I'LL BE COVERING A BUTTIGIEG
EVENT LATER ON TONIGHT.
THE THING ABOUT IOWA IS IT'S A
PLACE YOU CAN GO TO MOVE YOUR
POLLING NUMBERS, WHY BEING ON
THE GROUND MAKES A DIFFERENCE.
I CALL THESE THE SUPER VOTERS.
PARTICULARLY IN IOWA YOU MEET
THESE FOLKS WHO TAKE THEIR ROLES
SO SERIOUSLY.
LISTEN.
SIMPLY NAMING THEM ALL CAN BE A
FEAT.
>> PETE BUTTIGIEG, ELIZABETH
WARREN, AMY KLOBUCHAR.
>> BERNIE SANDERS, JULIAN CASTRO
AND INSLEE.
>> Reporter: MEETING AND
QUESTIONING THE DEMOCRATIC
CANDIDATES IS A DUTY AND A
PRIVILEGE.
HOW MANY OF THE DEMOCRATIC
CANDIDATES HAVE YOU GONE TO SEE
SO FAR?
>> I THINK BIDEN WILL BE 12.
>> Reporter: 12?
>> YES.
>> Reporter: VOTERS IN IOWA SEE
MOST OF THE CANDIDATES WITH MORE
THAN 150 EVENTS HELD IN THE
STATE IN THE MONTH ALONE.
>> I'LL TRAVEL TO WHEREVER WE
HAVE TO GO, YOU KNOW.
>> Reporter: SOME SUPER VOTERS
HAVE A CAUSE.
>> WHEN I STARTED IN 2016, I WAS
SO ANGRY.
>> SHE LOST HER HUSBAND TO
ALZHEIMER'S.
SHE'S ASKED OPPONENTS ABOUT THE
CAMPAIGN FOR TWO MONTHS.
>> MY HOPE IS THEY WOULD PUT OUT
A POLICY ABOUT ALZHEIMER'S.
>> Reporter: IN NEVADA, THERE IS
A GROUP CALLED MAKE THE ROAD.
>> I WANT TO BE AS PREPARED AS
POSSIBLE.
I DON'T WANT TO BE CAUGHT OFF
GUARD.
>> HE COMES TO THE RALLIES WITH
A LIST OF QUESTIONS.
WHAT IS YOUR METHOD TO GET A
CANDIDATE TO ANSWER YOUR
QUESTION?
>> TO CORNER THEM, IF THERE IS A
Q & A SESSION, MY ARM GOES UP
FASTER THAN ANYBODY ELSE'S.
I'VE BEEN TRAINED WELL.
>> Reporter: MARK CORVER HAS NO
PROBLEM CATCHING A CANDIDATE'S
EYE FOR A CHANCE TO GET A SIGNED
BASEBALL.
>> IT'S IMPORTANT TO GET
PERSONALIZED YOURSELF, BECAUSE
SOME PEOPLE THINK PRESIDENTS ARE
LARGER THAN LIFE.
THIS BRINGS OUT THE MORE HUMAN
SIDE.
>> Reporter: FOR ALL THESE SUPER
VOTERS, PICKING PRESIDENTS IS A
PARTICIPATORY SPORT.
WATCHING THE DEBATE ISN'T
ENOUGH.
THEY WANT TO SHAPE IT.
>> I'M ONE OF MANY VOICES, BUT
IF I HAVE A VOICE HERE IN NEW
HAMPSHIRE, I'M GOING TO USE IT
TO THE BEST OF MY ABILITY TO TRY
TO MAKE A CHANGE.
>> Reporter: CHRIS, TECHNOLOGY
HAS CHANGED THE GAME HERE, TOO.
THE EASE OF SHOOTING A VIDEO AND
POSTING IT ON SOCIAL MEDIA HAS
GIVEN THESE SUPERVOTERS EVEN
MORE POWER TO SHAPE THE NATURE
OF THESE DISCUSSIONS.
>> VAUGHN, IN THE SUNSHINE,
SHACK IS NEAR A COFFEE POT, SO
YOU TELL ME WHO HAS IT BEST.
>>> THE REQUEST OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S TAX RETURNS IS ON A
WHOLE NEW LEVEL AS THE DEMOCRATS
TURN TO A GAME-CHANGING THREAT.
T
I have one kid in each branch
of the military,
but I'm command central.
It's so important to us
that Verizon
is supporting military families.
When I have a child deployed,
having a reliable network
means everything.
So, when I get a video chat,
and I get to see their face,
it's the best thing
in the world.
And I've earned every one
of these gray hairs.
Military moms, we serve too.
(VO)
The network more people rely on,
gives you more.
Like military plans with
a special price on Unlimited,
$100 per line, and big savings
on our best phones
when you switch.
That's Verizon.
When you shop for
your home at Wayfair,
you get more than
FREE shipping.
You get everything
you need for
your home at a great price,
the way it works
best for you,
I'll take that. Wait honey, no.
when you want it.
You get a delivery
experience
you can always count on.
You get your perfect find at
a price to match,
on your own schedule.
You get FAST and FREE
shipping on the things that
make your home feel like you.
That's what you get
when you've got Wayfair.
So shop now!
If you live with diabetes,
why fingerstick when
you can scan?
With the FreeStyle
Libre 14 day system
just scan the sensor
with your reader,
iPhone or Android and
manage your diabetes.
With the FreeStyle
Libre 14 day system,
a continuous
glucose monitor,
you can check your
glucose levels any time,
without fingersticks.
Ask your doctor to
write a prescription for the
FreeStyle Libre
14 day system.
You can do it
without fingersticks.
Learn more at FreeStyleLibre.us
You can do it
without fingersticks.
Can you love
wearing powerful sunscreen?
Yes!
Neutrogena® Ultra Sheer®.
Unbeatable protection
helps prevent
early skin aging and skin cancer
with a clean feel.
The best for your skin.
Ultra Sheer®.
Neutrogena®.
Woman: (On phone) Discover.
Hi.
Do you have a travel card?
Yep. Our Miles card.
Earn unlimited 1.5 miles
and we'll match it at the
end of your first year.
Nice! I'm thinking about
a scuba diving trip.
Woman:
Ooh!
(Gasp)
Or not.
You okay?
Yeah, no, I'm good.
>>> NOW TO THAT BIG ESCALATION
IN THE CONGRESSIONAL DEMOCRATS'
FIGHT TO SEE PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
TAXES.
THE HOUSE IS SUING THE TREASURY
DEPARTMENT AND THE INTERNAL
REVENUE SERVICE OVER HIS RETURNS
AFTER THEIR REQUESTS AND THEN
SUBPOENAS OF THE RETURNS WAS
IGNORED BY TREASURY SECRETARY
STEVE MNUCHIN AND CHARLES
REDDIG.
NOW IT COULD ULTIMATELY BE
FOUGHT IN THE SUPREME COURT.
HE'S BEEN COVERING THIS FOR
MONTHS AND ALSO AN MSNBC
CONTRIBUTOR.
AND ALSO HE'S WRITTEN MULTIPLE
BOOKS ON THE PRESIDENT AND THE
ADMINISTRATION.
HE'S AN EXPERT ON TAX ISSUES AND
HAS BEEN LOOKING INTO THE
PRESIDENT'S TAXES FOR YEARS.
SO CHARLIE, THE WHITE HOUSE
REFUSAL TO COMPLY WITH THE
SUBPOENA IS, AND I'M QUOTING
HERE, AN EXTRAORDINARY ATTACK ON
THE AUTHORITY OF CONGRESS TO
OBTAIN INFORMATION NEEDED TO
CONDUCT OVERSIGHT OF TREASURY,
THE IRS, AND THE TAX LAWS.
SO WHAT IS THE WEIGHT OF THEM TO
COMPLY?
>> THEY'RE STONEWALLING CONGRESS
WHICH IS TO SAY ALL OF THEIR
REQUESTS ARE ILLEGITIMATE WILL
STAND JUDICIAL SCRUTINY.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION HAS
BEEN FIGHTING ALL SUBPOENAS AND
REQUEST FOR INFORMATION EVER
SINCE THE HOUSE WAS TAKEN OVER
BY DEMOCRATS SIX MONTHS AGO BY
SAYING THAT CONGRESS ONLY HAS
AUTHORITY TO REQUEST INFORMATION
IF IT'S THINKING ABOUT HOW TO
WRITE A NEW LAW, AND IT DOESN'T
HAVE AUTHORITY TO REQUEST
INFORMATION TO UNCOVER
WRONGDOING.
AND EVEN WHEN IT SAYS IT'S
TRYING TO WRITE A NEW LAW, THE
BRANCH CAN SAY THAT'S JUST A
PRETEXT.
THIS IS ABOUT EXPOSING
INFORMATION FOR POLITICAL
PURPOSES.
THAT'S OUTSIDE YOUR AUTHORITY
AND YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
TWO COURTS HAVE ALREADY REJECTED
THAT ARGUMENT AT THE DISTRICT
COURT LEVEL AND WILL OFFER
SUBPOENAS BY CONGRESS TO
FINANCIAL FIRMS FOR TRUMP
ORGANIZATION RECORDS.
NOW A THIRD JUDGE WILL GET A
CRACK AT IT, AND THIS IS THE
FIRST ONE COMING FROM CONGRESS
ITSELF.
>> HERE'S PART OF THE WHITE
HOUSE STATEMENT.
CHAIRMAN NEAL'S WILLINGNESS TO
USE HIS POWERFUL COMMITTEE TO GO
AFTER HIS POLITICAL OPPONENTS IS
A DANGEROUS DEMOCRACY.
THE COMMITTEE HAS NO LEGITIMATE
LEJS LAIFSH PURPOSE FOR WHICH IT
CAN DEMAND THE PRESIDENT'S TAX
RETURNS AND IT'S EVIDENT THEY
ARE ONLY INTERESTED IN PARTISAN
GAINS.
CHARLIE, IS THIS PARTISAN?
WHAT COULD BE IN THOSE RETURNS
THAT WOULD BE OF INTEREST TO
CONGRESS?
>> YOU WOULD HAVE TO BE UTTERLY
NAIVE TO THINK IT'S NOT
POLITICAL, OF COURSE IT'S
POLITICAL, IT'S JUST WHETHER
IT'S WITHIN CONGRESS' AUTHORITY
TO DO IT REGARDLESS OF ITS
MOEFSH.
ON THE FACE OF IT, THE LAW SAYS
THIS COMMITTEE CAN REQUEST ANY
INDIVIDUAL'S TAX RETURNS,
PERIOD.
IT DOESN'T SET A LIMIT.
SO THE EXECUTIVE BRANCH IS KIND
OF INVENTING ONE AND WE'LL SEE
WHETHER A JUDGE GOES ALONG WITH
THAT.
WHY WOULD THEY WANT IT?
THEY'VE SAID ON OTHER OCCASIONS
THAT THEY WANTED TO SEE THESE
RETURNS BECAUSE EVERY PRESIDENT
UNTIL NOW HAS RELEASED HIS
RETURNS AND THEY WANT TO ENFORCE
THAT TRADITION.
THEY WANT TO SEE WHAT KIND OF
FINANCIAL DEALINGS TRUMP HAS
THAT MAY HAVE RUN AFOUL OF THE
CONSTITUTION BORROWING AND
RECEIVING EMOLLUMENTS, AND THEY
WANT TO SEE WHAT THE PRESIDENT'S
FINANCIAL HEALTH IS AND WHETHER
IT LINES UP WITH WHAT HE CLAIMS
IT IS ON THE SCALE.
SO THERE'S ALL KINDS OF REASONS
THAT THEY WANT TO SEE THESE AND
THEY CLEARLY ALSO WANT TO MAKE
THEM PUBLIC.
>> BUT DAVID, WHAT THEY WANT TO
PUT OUT THERE IS THE REASON THEY
DON'T THINK THEY SHOULD TURN
THEM OVER AND KIND OF PROTECTING
THE OFFICE, NOT PROTECTING
SOMETHING THAT MIGHT BE IN THERE
THAT WOULD LEAD TO PROBLEMS FOR
THE PRESIDENT.
TELL US IN CONTEXT WHAT YOU KNOW
ABOUT THE PRESIDENT'S RETURNS
AND WHAT MIGHT BE IN THERE.
>> ALL THE ARGUMENTS BEING MADE
BY THE ADMINISTRATION ARE SIMPLY
COVER FOR HIDING TRUMP'S TAX
RETURNS.
AND THE ARGUMENT THAT THE
COURT'S GOING TO HEAR IS THAT
TRUMP HIMSELF HAS MADE THE CASE
THAT THERE IS A LEGITIMATE
PURPOSE.
HE SAID HE'S BEEN AUDITED BY THE
IRS.
HE CLAIMS HE'S BEING AUDITED
BECAUSE HE'S A CHRISTIAN.
HE CLAIMS HE'S BEING TREATED
DIFFERENTLY THAN OTHER
PRESIDENTS.
SO HE, IN HIS OWN WORDS, HAS
MADE THE CASE HERE THAT CONGRESS
SHOULD BE LOOKING AT THIS AS
PART OF THE OVERSIGHT OF THE
INTERNAL REVENUE SERVICE.
IN THE HISTORY OF THIS LAW WHICH
WAS ENACTED IN 1924, THERE HAS
NOT BEEN A SINGLE CASE OF THE
IRS NOT TURNING OVER INFORMATION
WHEN REQUESTED.
IN FACT, THE JOINT COMMITTEE ON
TAXATION HAS THREE STAFF MEMBERS
WHO WORK IN THE IRS BUILDING
BECAUSE THEY REVIEW TAX RETURNS
EVERY DAY OF THE WEEK.
>> SO MICK MULVANEY, TRUMP'S
ACTING CHIEF OF STAFF, HAS SAID
THAT THE DEMOCRATS WILL NEVER
SEE TRUMP'S TAX RETURNS.
DAIFRD, IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU
WOULDN'T PLACE A BET ON THAT.
>> THEY WILL SEE TRUMP'S TAX
RETURNS.
IF THIS ISN'T SETTLED BY THE END
OF THIS CONGRESS, THE CLOCK WILL
HAVE TO START WITH NEW
LITIGATION, BUT WE WILL
EVENTUALLY SEE TRUMP'S TAX
RETURNS, NO QUESTION ABOUT IT,
AND IN ADDITION THE NEW YORK
STATE LEGISLATURE AND THE
GOVERNOR WHO SIGNED LEGISLATION
THAT PROVIDES TO THE WAYS AND
MEANS COMMITTEE AND OTHER
CONGRESSIONAL TAX COMMITTEES THE
NEW YORK STATE INFORMATION FROM
TRUMP'S TAX RETURNS.
PEOPLE WATCHING SHOULDN'T
FORGET, TRUMP WON'T EVEN RELEASE
THE AUDIT LETTER, ABSOLUTELY
ADODINE DOCUMENT THAT CLAIMS
HE'S BEEN AUDITED.
THEY HAVE STRONG REASON TO
BELIEVE IT'S TAX SHEETS BUT THEY
HAVEN'T NAILED THE CASE YET.
>> SO CHARLIE, WHEN MIGHT WE GET
SOMETHING ON THIS?
WHEN MIGHT THIS ALL BE SETTLED?
COULD IT INDEED GO PAST 2020?
>> EASILY.
A DISTRICT COURT JUDGE HAS TO
LOOK AT IT.
ASSUMING TRUMP LOSES, HE'LL
APPEAL.
AN APPEALS COURT WILL HAVE TO
LOOK AT IT.
WHOEVER LOSES THAT WILL APPEAL
TO THE FULL APPEALS COURT.
TO THE SUPREME COURT.
IT'S VERY EASY TO SEE THIS
DRAGGING ON FOR A LONG TIME.
ON THE OTHER HAND, THOSE TWO
CASES I MENTIONED EARLIER
INVOLVING SUBPOENAS TO PRIVATE
BANKING FIRMS, THE LINE JUDGES
WHO LOOKED AT BOTH OF THOSE
CASES REMOVED THEM VERY QUICKLY.
IN A MATTER OF WEEKS THEY SAID,
NO, TRUMP IS WRONG AND ORDERED
THE FIRMS TO COMPLY AND THEN
TRUMP APPEALED.
IT'S POSSIBLE THAT JUDGES CAN
CHOOSE TO MOVE THIS ALONG AND
NOT LET IT BE DRAGGED OUT, BUT
FOR NOW IT'S CLEARLY THE
STRATEGY OF THE TRUMP LEGAL TEAM
TO JUST BUY TIME AND STALL.
>> CHARLIE SAVAGE, DAVID CAY
JOHNSON, GOOD TO SEE BOTH OF
YOU.
>>> AHEAD OF TOMORROW'S
ACTIVITIES, WHY SOME MILITARY
OFFICIALS ARE EXPRESSING
CONCERNS ABOUT PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
CONTROVERSIAL FOURTH OF JULY
CELEBRATION.
NT TRUMP'S
CONTROVERSIAL FOURTH OF JULY
CELEBRATION.
the clock is ticking on
irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
HUMIRA can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
HUMIRA targets and blocks a
source of inflammation
that contributes to joint pain
and irreversible damage.
HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections
including tuberculosis,
and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened;
as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor if
you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Help stop the clock
on further irreversible
joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here. Right now.
HUMIRA.
I switched to MiraLAX
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives
forcefully stimulate
the nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX works with
the water in your
body to unblock your
system naturally.
And it doesn't cause
bloating,
cramping, gas,
or sudden urgency.
MiraLAX.
Look for the pink cap.
Make fitness routine
with Pure Protein.
High protein.
Low sugar.
Tastes great!
High protein.
Low sugar.
So good!
High protein.
Low sugar.
Mmmm,
Birthday cake!
Pure Protein.
The best combination for
every fitness routine.
You've tried so many
moisturizers...
but one blows them all
out of the water.
Hydro Boost with hyaluronic acid
to plump skin cells
so it bounces back...
Neutrogena®
And try our hydrating makeup.
>>> SO HERE'S THE PROMISE THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS TWEETING THIS
MORNING.
HE'LL GIVE THE U.S., QUOTE, A
SHOW OF A LIFETIME AT TOMORROW'S
EXPANDED JULY FOURTH CELEBRATION
IN WASHINGTON.
HERE'S ONE LOOK AT HOW THAT'S
COMING ALONG.
POLITICO'S HEATHER CAGEL TWEETED
THAT A CRANE HAD TO BE USED TO
GET AROUND THE WHITE HOUSE.
THERE IS ALSO A REPORT THAT THE
EXTRAVAGANZA THAT HE'S WANTED TO
HAVE FOR TWO YEARS NOW WILL
BALLOON TO $25 MILLION AND WILL
MEAN LESS MONEY FOR THE NATIONAL
PARKS.
THE NATIONAL PARKS HAS DIVERTED
$2.5 MILLION IN FEES TO COVER
SOME OF THE COSTS.
MONICA ALBA JOINS US NOW WITH
MORE FROM THE CAPITOL MALL.
WE KNOW THE PENTAGON HAS
SCRAMBLED TO GET TOGETHER ON
SHORT NOTICE WHAT THE WHITE
HOUSE NEEDS.
WHAT ARE YOU SEEING ON THE
GROUND?
>> Reporter: YOU CAN SEE RIGHT
HERE NEXT TO ME, THESE ARE
ACTUALLY TWO BRADLEY FIGHTING
VEHICLES.
THIS IS JUST SOME OF THE
MILITARY MIGHT THAT IS EXPECTED
TO BE ON FULL DISPLAY TOMORROW
NIGHT HERE, OF COURSE, ON THE
NATIONAL MALL RIGHT BEHIND ME.
THIS IS JUST SOME OF AN EXAMPLE.
YOU MENTIONED THAT THEY WERE
MOVED OVERNIGHT ON TRAINS AND ON
FLATBED TRUCKS BECAUSE THESE
TANKS ARE SO HEAVY.
THE PRESIDENT FELL IN LOVE WITH
THIS TWO YEARS AGO IN PARIS ON
BASTILLE DAY AND WANTED TO
RECREATE IT, BUT A LOT OF
CRITICS ARE QUESTIONING WHETHER
HE'LL BE ABLE TO KEEP THIS EVENT
THAT IS TYPICALLY NONPARTISAN
PARTISAN, WHETHER HE'LL GO INTO
A CAMPAIGN MODE.
WHEN ASKED ABOUT THE SPEECH HE'S
GOING TO GIVE, WHETHER IT WILL
UNIFY ALL AMERICANS, HE SAID, I
THINK SO, BUT HE'S GOING TO TALK
ABOUT THE DEMOCRATS.
TOURISTS ARE HERE.
IT'S JUST ANOTHER HOT SUMMER
DAY.
TOMORROW THIS WILL LOOK
DIFFERENT WITH MANY PEOPLE
EXPECTED ON THE MALL.
CHRIS?
>> MONICA ALBA, THANK YOU FOR
THAT.
PHIL RUCKER IS BACK WITH ME AS
WELL AS JACK JACOBS, A MEDAL
AFTER HONOR RECIPIENT AND MSNBC
MILITARY CONTRIBUTOR.
PHIL, YOU SAID, QUOTE, THIS
YEAR'S GATHERING ON THE MALL
MARKS A DEPARTURE BECAUSE
PRESIDENTS TYPICALLY HAVE NOT
PARTICIPATED IN INDEPENDENCE DAY
CELEBRATIONS.
WHY INDEPENDENCE DAY IF YOU'RE
DOING A MILITARY PARADE?
WHAT ARE YOU HEARING ABOUT ALL
THIS, BECAUSE IT WAS ALL PRETTY
FAST.
>> THE PRESIDENT WANTED TO DO A
MILITARY PARADE AND THOSE PLANS
WERE THWARTED BY THE GOVERNMENT
OVER CONCERNS ABOUT COST AND
JUST INFRASTRUCTURE PROBLEMS
WITH ROLLING TANKS THROUGH THE
STREETS OF A CITY.
SO THE PARADE WAS NOT TO BE.
THE PRESIDENT SEIZED ON THIS
JULY 4th MOMENT AS A CHANCE TO
PUT HIS OWN MARK ON WHAT HAS
HISTORICALLY BEEN A DECIDEDLY
NONPARTISAN CELEBRATION IN THE
NATION'S CAPITOL.
HE'S WANTED TO HAVE BIGGER
FIREWORKS THAN NORMAL, HE'S
WANTED TO PUT HIMSELF AT CENTER
STAGE, HE'S GIVEN OUT VIP
TICKETS TO HIS POLITICAL DONORS,
AND MEANWHILE IT'S BEING FUNDED
BY THE GOVERNMENT, NOT BY HIS
CAMPAIGN.
AND IN FACT MY COLLEAGUES AT THE
POST HAVE REPORTED LAST NIGHT
THAT $2.5 MILLION ON NATIONAL
PARK ENTRY FEES, THESE ARE THE
FEES YOU PAY WHEN YOU GO TO
VISIT YOSEMITE OR YELLOWSTONE OR
ANY OF THESE NATIONAL PARKS,
THAT THAT MONEY HAS BEEN
DIVERTED AWAY FROM THE PARKS TO
HELP FUND TOMORROW'S
CELEBRATION.
>> THERE ARE, COLONEL, AS YOU
KNOW, RUSSIA HAS VICTORY DAY, WE
MENTIONED HE WAS AT BASTILLE DAY
WHERE HE KIND OF GOT THE IDEA
THAT HE WANTED THIS.
DO YOU SHARE THE CONCERNS WE'VE
HEARD FROM FORMER MILITARY
OFFICERS THAT, LOOK, YOU HAVE TO
KEEP THIS STUFF APOLITICAL, AND
IT CLEARLY IS NOT?
>> I DO, AND PEOPLE I'VE TALKED
TO DO AS WELL.
WE'VE HAD A LONG HISTORY
TRADITION OF AGO AN APOLITICAL
FOURTH OF JULY CELEBRATION.
WE'RE CELEBRATING THE FOUNDER OF
THE COUNTRY, NOT CELEBRATING OUR
MILITARY MIGHT.
THE THING THAT CONCERNS ME THE
MOST IS THE FACT THAT WE DON'T
HAVE TO SHOW OUR MILITARY MIGHT.
YOU KNOW, THERE ARE TANK
COUNTRIES AND THERE ARE NON TANK
COUNTRIES.
WE ARE A NON-TANK COUNTRIES.
IRAN IS A TANK COUNTRY.
NORTH KOREA, RUSSIA, CHINA,
THOSE ARE ALL TANK COUNTRIES.
WE DON'T HAVE TO DEMONSTRATE --
AS A MATTER OF FACT, IT'S PART
OF OUR STRENGTH THAT WE DON'T
HAVE TO DEMONSTRATE OUR STRENGTH
IN THIS WAY.
AND THE CONCLUSION THAT ONE
DRAWS IS THAT THIS IS MERELY
A -- IT'S NOT EVEN A THINLY
VEILED CAMPAIGN EVENT, IT LOOKS
EXACTLY LIKE A CAMPAIGN EVENT
AND IT PANDERS TO THE LEAST
SAVORY OF ALL OF OUR POLITICAL
NOTIONS, CHRIS.
>> WELL, THE OTHER THING, I
THINK, THAT WE'RE SEEING A
LITTLE BIT HERE, PHIL, IS THAT
THIS IS IN SOME WAYS NOT UNLIKE
THE PRESIDENT TWEETING THAT HE'D
LIKE TO MEET KIM JONG-UN AT THE
DMZ, AND THEN THERE'S A BIG
SCRAMBLING.
THE PRESS SECRETARY GETS CAUGHT
IN THE MIDDLE OF IT AND ALL
THESE THINGS NEED TO GET DONE AT
THE LAST MINUTE.
IT SOUNDS LIKE THAT'S WHAT
HAPPENED WITH PENTAGON IN THIS
CASE.
>> CHRIS, I THINK WHAT'S GOING
ON HERE IS THE PRESIDENT HIMSELF
IS TRYING TO PRODUCE THIS EVENT.
REMEMBER, HIS BACKGROUND IS IN
PUTTING ON REALITY TELEVISION
SHOWS.
HE CARES INTENSELY ABOUT THE
STAGING OF HIS POLITICAL
RALLIES, ABOUT WHAT GOES WHERE,
WHAT EQUIPMENT WOULD BE
INVOLVED.
HE'S BEEN VERY HANDS-ON IN THE
LAST FEW WEEKS IN PUTTING
TOGETHER THE PLANS FOR THE
FOURTH OF JULY ON THE MALL.
>> CURRENTLY JACK, DOES IT
BOTHER YOU WITH EVERYTHING THAT
IS GOING ON IN THE WORLD,
MULTIPLE NUCLEAR THREATS AMONG
THEM, THAT THIS IS HOW THE
PRESIDENT IS SPENDING HIS TIME?
>> WELL, OF COURSE, IT'S
BOTHERSOME, BUT DON'T FORGET --
LOOK, HE'S NOT ALONE.
ALL PRESIDENTS ARE ALWAYS
CAMPAIGNING, ALWAYS HAVE BEEN.
BUT THIS IS REALLY IN YOUR FACE,
AND IT'S CLEAR THAT HIS FOCUS IS
LESS CLEAR ON THE KIND OF THINGS
THAT KEEP US FREE THAN THINGS
THAT LOOK LIKE THEY KEEP US
FREE.
YOU JUST HAVE TO GO BACK A
COUPLE WEEKS AND TAKE A LOOK AT
THE POSITIVITY OF INTELLIGENT
AND STRATEGIC DECISION MAKING
TAKING PLACE JUST IN THE LAST
FEW WEEKS WITH IRAN BEING
AGGRESSIVE IN THE GULF, THE
ATTACKS ON THE SHIPS THERE,
WHAT'S TAKEN PLACE IN IRAN NOW,
PLUS UPPING ITS NUCLEAR
CAPABILITY.
NO RESPONSE FROM THE UNITED
STATES TO SPEAK OF.
SAME THING IN KOREA AND NORTH
KOREA, CHINA SPREADING OUT
ACROSS THE SOUTH CHINA SEA AND
SO ON.
THERE ARE LOTS AND LOTS OF
THINGS WE NEED TO DO WITH OUR
MILITARY.
THIS ISN'T ONE OF THEM.
>> COLONEL JACK JACOBS, ALWAYS
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
HAPPY FOURTH, AND TO YOU, PHIL
RUCKER, AS WELL.
THANKS, GUYS.
>>> UP NEXT, IT MIGHT NOT COME
AS A SURPRISE THAT POLLS SHOW
ELIZABETH WARREN AND KAMALA
HARRIS GETTING A BUMP AFTER
THEIR DEBATE PERFORMANCES, BUT A
NEW ANALYSIS SHOWS EXACTLY WHERE
THEIR GAINS ARE COMING FROM.
>>> THIS MORNING A NEW
WASHINGTON POST/ABC POLL SHOWS
WHILE KAMALA HARRIS AND
ELIZABETH WARREN DID GET A
BOOST, JOE BIDEN STILL LEADS.
AND THAT LEAD HAS DIMINISHED,
THOUGH HE REMAINS AT THE TOP OF
EVERY NATIONAL POLL WE HAVE SEEN
SINCE THE DEBATES.
THIS MORNING WE MAY KNOW WHY.
IT GOES BEYOND IOWA AND BEYOND
THE NOMINATION.
45% OF VOTERS THINK THAT HE IS
THE CANDIDATE WHO CAN BEAT TRUMP
IN THE GENERAL LOCATION.
JOINING ME TO WEIGH IN IS
FOUNDER OF PULSO, A SOCIAL
MEDIA.
TYLER ARE BACK WITH ME.
DOUG, DO YOU THINK IT'S THAT
SIMPLE?
BIDEN IS STILL IN THE LEAD
BECAUSE HE IS VIEWED AS MORE
MODERATE AND DEMOCRATS THINK HE
CAN WIN IN THE GENERAL?
>> WELL, I THINK IT IS BECAUSE
HE HAS A BROAD COALITION OF
SUPPORT.
AFRICAN-AMERICANS HAVE BEEN A
BASE OF HIS SUPPORT SINCE HE
STARTED.
HE'S DOING WELL WITH OLDER
VOTERS.
HE'S DOING WELL WITH MODERATE
SO HE'S GOT A BROADER COALITION.
DEPENDING WHAT POLLS YOU LOOK
AT, THEY ARE SAYING DIFFERENT
THINGS.
I WOULD JUST BE CAUTIOUS ABOUT
INTERPRETING THEM TOO MUCH UNTIL
A COUPLE WEEKS AFTER THE DEBATES
HAVE PASSED.
>> WELL, LET ME SHOW YOU
SOMETHING, THOUGH.
THIS IS INTERESTING.
5:38 DID SOMETHING REALLY SMART.
THEY TOOK A GROUP OF VOTERS
BEFORE THE DEBATES AND POLLED
THEM.
THEN THEY DID ONE AFTER THE
DEBATE.
SO YOU ACTUALLY SEE HOW THE
DEBATES MOVED THINGS.
THE BIG WINNER, KAMALA HARRIS UP
9.4.
JULIAN CASTRO, ELIZABETH WARREN
ALSO GAINING.
DOWN IS JOE BIDEN, BETO O'ROURKE
AND PETE BUTTIGIEG.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THAT, LIZ?
>> I WOULD SAY THERE ARE SEVERAL
POLLS THAT WE SHOULD BE LOOKING
AT.
THE POLL THAT CAME OUT YESTERDAY
THAT SURVEYED VOTERS SHOWED THAT
KAMALA HARRIS WENT UP FROM SIXTH
PLACE UP TO FIRST AND JULIAN
CASTRO HAD A BIG JUMP.
WE KNOW THAT THE LATIN COMMUNITY
WILL BE THE LARGEST MINORITY
VOTING BLOC IN 2020.
>> HOW DO WE KNOW THAT?
HOW DO WE KNOW THAT?
>> WELL, MANY STUDIES HAVE SHOWN
OUR COMMUNITY IS INCREASING NOT
ONLY IN VOTING AGE BUT NUMBERS
OVERALL.
WILL 00,000 EVERY SINGLE DAY.
SO WE KNOW THE CANDIDATE THAT IS
ELECTED IN 2020 IN THE
DEMOCRATIC PRIMARIES WILL NOT
WIN THE GENERAL ELECTION.
>> SO THERE IS A LOT OF TALK
ABOUT, YOU KNOW, WHO WON, WHO
LOST AND, RICK, I THINK THESE
POLLS AREN'T JUST BEING WATCHED
CLOSELY BY THESE CAMPAIGNS BUT
BY THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN.
WHAT DO THEY TAKE AWAY FROM WHAT
WE HAVE SEEN SO FAR?
>> WELL, I THINK JOE BIDEN HAS
BEEN MOVED.
HARRIS IS RIGHT WHERE SHE WANTS
TO BE BECAUSE YOU DO NOT WANT TO
BE THE FRONT RUNNER THIS EARLY
O.
>> WOULDN'T TRUMP RATHER RUN
AGAINST HER THAN BIDEN?
>> IT'S TOO EARLY TO SAY.
THE LEADERS WILL SHIFT A LITTLE
BIT.
LOST GROUND IN EVERY
DEMOGRAPHIC.
IT PROBABLY CAME OUT OF JOE
BIDEN.
ELIZABETH WARREN WAS FLAT
ACTUALLY.
SHE LOST SIGNIFICANT SUPPORT.
JOE BIDEN STILL REMAINS THE TOP
OF THE HEAP AND THE PERSON
BELIEVE WILL BEAT DONALD TRUMP.
KAMALA HARRIS HAS IMPROVED
SIGNIFICANTLY IN HER
BELIEVABILITY SHE CAN BEAT
DONALD TRUMP.
THAT IS A HUGE FACTOR THIS TIME
AROUND.
>> OBVIOUSLY, DOUG, YOU HAVE TO
BUILD A WINNING COALITION.
A NEW PIECE BY ALEX SIGHTSWALD
WHO WRITES HARRIS STUNNED BIDEN
BUT CAN SHE WIN AN OBAMA
COALITION?
FROM YOUR PERSPECTIVE AT THIS
POINT, WHO IS DOING THE RIGHT
THINGS TO GO IN THAT DIRECTION.
>> YOU START PUTTING ORGANIZERS
ON THE GROUND.
KAMALA HARRIS'S CAMPAIGN IS
DOING THAT MORE AND MORE IN IOWA
AND SOUTH CAROLINA.
ELIZABETH WARREN HAS A HUGE
FIELD STAFF SHE HAS INVESTED IN
A NUMBER OF KEY EARLY STATES.
SO HAVING THAT DIRECT
PERSON-TO-PERSON COMMUNICATION
IS REALLY IMPORTANT IN TERMS OF
BUILDING OUT YOUR COALITION.
WHEN THE CANDIDATES START TO
ADVERTISE AND GET THEIR MESSAGE
OUT, THAT'S GOING TO BE REALLY
IMPORTANT.
BUT, LOOK, I WOULD JUST -- I
WOULD TAKE ISSUE WITH ONE THING
THAT RICK SAID.
I THINK WITH KAMALA HARRIS, YOU
KNOW, THERE WAS A LOT OF ROOM TO
GROW.
A LOT OF PEOPLE DIDN'T KNOW HER
OR ELIZABETH WARREN.
BOTH DID VERY WELL.
LIZ WETTING WARREN DID WELL AS
WELL.
>> SEIZE THE DAY, RIGHT?
THANKS TO ALL OF YOU.
HAPPY FOURTH.
>> RASHIDA TALIB WILL BE HERE TO
TALK ABOUT THE DETENTION CENTERS
AND WHAT SHE WITNESSED.
ENTION CS
AND WHAT SHE WITNESSED
Make fitness routine
with Pure Protein.
High protein.
Low sugar.
Tastes great!
High protein.
Low sugar.
So good!
High protein.
Low sugar.
Mmmm,
Birthday cake!
Pure Protein.
The best combination for
every fitness routine.
The best way
to hit the beach?
With Neutrogena®
Beach Defense® sunscreen.
Helioplex® powered,
UVA, UVB strong.
Beach strength protection
for the whole family.
For the best day in the sun.
Neutrogena®.
>>> THAT WRAPS UP THIS HOUR.
COMING UP RIGHT NOW, MORE NEWS
WITH HALLIE JACKSON.
HEY, HALLIE.
>> KRIS, THANK YOU SO MUCH ON
THIS HOLIDAY WEDNESDAY.
BREAKING NEWS OUT OF THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION.