McCONNELL IS WATCHING TODAY.
THANK YOU ALL, AS THIS 4th OF
JULY, WE ARE CELEBRATING
AMERICA, THAT DOES IT FOR THIS
EDITION OF "ANDREA MITCHELL
REPORTS."
HERE IS ALI VELSHI FROM "VELSHI
& RUHLE."
>> HELLO EVERYONE, THE CRISIS AT
THE BORDER, WE GOT NEW DETAILS
ABOUT HOW CHILDREN ARE BEING
TREATED AND U.S. CUSTODY WOULD
BE CONSIDERED AS ABUSE IF IT
HAPPENS AT HOME.
PLUS, PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS HE'S
CUTTING PRESCRIPTION DRUG
PRICES.
THOUSANDS ARE SKYROCKETING.
WE'LL DIG INTO THE NUMBERS FOR
YOU.
MILITARY TANKS HAVE ARRIVED ON
THE NATIONAL MALL FOR THE
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S 4th OF JULY
CELEBRATION.
WE'LL LOOK AT THE COSTS AND
CONCERNS FROM THE PENTAGON.
TODAY PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
INSISTING HIS FIGHT FOR
ADDING -- THE NEWS REPORTS ABOUT
DEPARTMENT OF COMMERCE DROPPING
ITS QUEST TO CITIZENSHIP
QUESTION ON THE CENSUS IS
INCORRECT.
WILBUR ROSS WHO SAYS 24 HOURS
AGO THIS.
"THE CENSUS BURR RHEE HAS
STARTED THE PROCESS OF PRINTING
THE QUESTIONNAIRES WITHOUT THE
QUESTION.
MY FOCUS AND THAT OF THE BUREAU
AND THE ENTIRE DEPARTMENT IS TO
CONDUCT A COMPLETE AND ACCURATE
CENSUS.
FOLLOWING THE SUPREME COURT'S
DECISION TO BLOCK THE QUESTIONS
FROM 2020 CENSUS.
KELLY O'DONELL IS JOINING ME.
THIS ONE IS A TRICKY ONE.
THE COMMERCE DEPARTMENT ACTUALLY
HAS TO PRINT THE CENSUS AND THE
CENSUS ACTUALLY HAS TO GO OUT.
THIS ONE SEEMS TO BE EASY TO
IDENTIFY WHAT THE STORY ACTUALLY
IS.
WHY ARE THE PRESIDENT AND THE
CONGRESS DEPARTMENT IS NOT ON
THE SAME PAGE ABOUT THIS.
YOU CAN ARGUE THERE ARE TWO
DIFFERENT TRACKS.
THERE IS THE PRACTICAL PIECE
HAVING TO PRINT THE CENSUS AND
IN THIS CASE NO QUESTIONS ABOUT
CITIZENSHIP FOR THOSE WHO
PARTICIPATE.
2020 IS KNOCKING ON OUR DOOR.
WILBUR ROSS AND SECRETARY'S OWN
NAME.
YOU READ THE STATEMENT.
THIS IS CLEARLY COMING FROM THE
DEPARTMENT OF COMMERCE.
SO WHERE IS THE SECOND LEVEL,
YOU COULD CONTINUE THE LEGAL
CHALLENGE AND MAKE IT AN ISSUE
AND COULD BE RESOLVED AT A LATER
DATE OR ARGUABLY YOU COULD SAY
REPRINT THE PORTIONS OF THE
CENSUS OR THE NEXT CENSUS.
IT APPEARS TO BE POLITICAL
MESSAGING THAT THE PRESIDENT IS
TAKING A STRONG POSITION ON
THIS.
JUST MONDAY HE WAS ASKED ABOUT
THIS QUESTION IN THE OVAL OFFICE
WOULD WE DELAY THE CENSUS.
HE SAID HE WAS STRONGLY LOOKING
AT THAT.
THE PRESIDENT WANTING TO STICK
WITH THAT POSITION BELIEING HE
EXPLAINS IN THE OVAL THAT THIS
IS AS QUESTION THAT HE BELIEVES
IT IS APPROPRIATE AND THE
COUNTRY'S RIGHTS TO KNOW WHO
AMONG THOSE PARTICIPATING IS A
CITIZEN WHO'S NOT.
HE DID NOT LEAVE OPEN THE
POSSIBILITY FOR NON CITIZENS WHO
HAVE PERMANENT LEGAL STATUS IN
THE UNITED STATES OR THOSE UNDER
PROTECTED STATUS LIKE ASYLUM
SEEKER.
HE JUST HAD EITHER/OR.
THE PRESIDENT IS STILL SAYING HE
WANTS TO FIGHT THIS FIGHT.
THERE IS A WAY FOR BOTH TO BE
TRUE BUT WE HAVE NOT YET HEARD
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE IS THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAVE A DIFFERENCE ON
THE ACTUAL PRINTING PART OF IT.
IT WOULD APPEAR THAT SHIP IS
ABOUT TO SAIL FROM ONE OF HIS
CLOSEST ADVISERS, WILBUR ROSS,
THAT IT IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> KELLY O'DONELL FOR US AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
CELEBRATING THE ACQUITTAL OF A
NAVY SEAL ACCUSED OF MURDERING
AN ISIS FIGHTER.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS
CONGRATULATIONS TO NAVY SEAL
EDDIE GALLAGHER.
YOU HAVE BEEN THROUGH MUCH
TOGETHER.
GLAD THAT I CAN HELP.
HE POSED FOR A PICTURE WITH THE
CORPSE.
HE WAS FOUND NOT GUILTY ON SIX
CRIMINAL CHARGES, HE WAS FOUND
GUILTY POSING WITH THE PHOTO'S
CASUALTIES.
HE WAS THE ONE WHO KILLED THE
BOY BY BLOCKING HIS BREATHING
TUBE IN AN ACT OF MERCY.
JOINING ME NOW FROM SAN DIEGO,
STEVE PATTPATTERSON.
WHAT HELP IS THE PRESIDENT
TALKING ABOUT IN THAT TWEET?
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT IS
REFERRING TO AN ACT THAT
OCCURRED IN THE PAST.
THERE WAS ABOUT A NINE-MONTH
PERIOD AFTER GALLAGHER WAS
ARRESTED FOR THESE WAR CRIMES IN
2017 DUTY IN MOSUL, IRAQ, WHERE
HE WAS TAKEN TO A MILITARY BRIG,
ARRESTED IN THE FALL AND I
BELIEVE RESIDENCE TAKEN AND
CONFINED THERE FOR A PERIOD OF
NEARLY A YEAR, ABOUT NINE
MONTHS.
THE PRESIDENT TAKES CREDIT FOR
MOVING HIM OUT OF THE BRIG AND
BACK HOME SAYING THAT THE BRIG
IS ONLY FOR PEOPLE THAT WERE A
FLIGHT RISK OR HAVE SIGNIFICANT
RISK OF HARMING SOMEONE OR
THEMSELVES OR OBVIOUSLY LEAVING
THE COUNTRY.
HIS ARGUMENT WAS THAT GALLAGHER
WAS AT RISK OF DOING NONE OF
THAT.
HE REFERENCED THIS AS HE DOES
WITH MOST EVERYTHING IN A TWEET
SAYING "IN HONOR OF HIS PAST
SERVICE TO OUR COUNTRY, EDDIE
GALLAGHER WILL SOON BE MOVED TO
A LESS RESTRICTIVE REFINEMENT.
THE PROCESS WILL MOVE QUICKLY."
WE SPOKE TO MEMBERS OF
GALLAGHER'S DEFENSE TEAM ON THE
WAY INTO COURT THIS MORNING.
THEY WERE PRAISING AND THANKING
PRESIDENT TRUMP FOR DOING THIS.
THANKS TO THE PRESIDENT THAT HE
ALLOWED ALL THIS PRESS TO USHER
IN BECAUSE OF HIS EXPOSURE TO
THE CASE.
SO THEY'RE VERY HAPPY WITH THE
ATTENTION THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS
GIVEN THIS CASE AND OBVIOUSLY
FOR WHATEVER HE DID TO MOVE
GALLAGHER FROM CONFINEMENT TO
HOME SO THEY CAN PREPARE FOR THE
TRIAL THAT WE JUST EXPERIENCED.
>> STEV PATTERSON FOR US IN LOS
ANGELES.
>>> THE RACE TO THE WHITE HOUSE,
SEVERAL CANDIDATES ARE
CAMPAIGNING IN IOWA.
BIDEN ANNOUNCED JUST RAISED
$21.5 MILLION IN THE SECOND
QUARTER ALONE.
THIS IS KAMALA HARRIS, A NEW
POLL SHOWS HARRIS IS UP 13
POINTS IN THE LAST THREE WEEKS
AND FRONT RUNNER BIDEN IS DOWN 8
POINTS.
HARRIS IS RESISTANTS AT 20% AND
BIDEN AT 22%.
SENATOR ELIZABETH WARREN AND
BERNIE SANDERS FOLLOWED.
WHEN VOTERS WERE ASKED WHO HAS
THE BEST CHANCE OF WINNING
AGAINST PRESIDENT TRUMP, BIDEN
MAINTAINS A STRONG 42% AND
HARRIS AT 14%.
THE BIGGEST JUMP AGAINST BELONG
TO SENATOR HARRIS.
SENATOR BERNIE SANDERS HOLDS
ONTO SECOND PLACE.
JOINING ME NOW FROM IOWA, OUR
ROAD WARRIORS, MIKE, YOU ARE
FOLLOWING JOE BIDEN, LET'S TALK
ABOUT THE SECOND QUARTER FOR HIM
IN TERMS OF FUND RAISING
COMPARES TO OTHER CANDIDATES WE
KNOW SO FAR.
>> Reporter: THE DOWNSIDE OF
BEING THE FRONT RUNNER IN THAT
DEBATE, JOE BIDEN PUT ON
DEFENSIVE BY SOME OF HIS
OPPONENTS.
AS HE ARRIVED TODAY SINCE THE
DEBATE A LITTLE BIT OF A SHOW OF
FORCE FOR THE BIDEN CAMPAIGN
ANNOUNING THE SECOND QUARTER
NUMBER.
IT IS NOT AS MUCH AS PETE
BUTTIGIEG RAISING MORE THAN
$25 MILLION.
BERNIE SANDERS WITH A BIG NUMBER
OF $18 MILLION.
THAT'S MORE ON A CURVE DAY BASES
THE BIDEN CAMPAIGN POINTS OUT.
I WILL READ A FEW OF THESE
STATISTICS HIGHLIGHTED BINOMIAL
Y BIDEN.
97% OF ALL DONATIONS ARE FROM
GRASS ROOT DONORS, AMOUNTS OF
LESS THAN $200 OR LESS.
THEY HAVE MORE THAN 256,000
DONORS.
OBVIOUSLY, ALI, AS BIDEN, HAVING
TO DEAL WITH THAT TENSE DEBATE
EXCHANGE WITH KAMALA HARRIS.
THE FACT THAT HE'S NOT GOING
ANYWHERE.
A REMINDER FROM THE BIDEN
CAMPAIGN AS WELL.
HIS DOLLAR IS GOING LONGER
BECAUSE HE GOT UNIVERSAL NAME
ID.
HE DOES NOT NEED TO SPEND THAT
NAME ON TV ADS ESTABLISHING TO
HIS VOTERS.
HE CAN INVEST IT ALL IN HIS
GRASS ROOTS.
VAUGHAN HILLIARD, YOU ARE
COVERING KAMALA HARRIS' EVENT IN
IOWA TODAY.
BIDEN CONTINUES TO LEAD WITH 24%
AND HARRIS AT SECOND PLACE AT
16%.
WHAT'S HER PLAN TO CLOSE THE GAP
AND KEEP THE MOMENTUM.
IT IS AN IMPORTANT QUESTION.
KAMALA HARRIS TENDS TO HAVE
MOMENTS AND SHE GOT THE FILL UP
THE SPACE IN BETWEEN THOSE
MOMENTS TO KEEP THAT MOMENTUM
GOING.
>> YEAH, YOU ARE FILLING THE
SPACE BY CAMPAIGNING.
SHE'S HERE IN DES MOINES.
SHE WILL BE APPEARING HERE AT
THIS PARK BEHIND US HERE IN JUST
ABOUT AN HOUR BEFORE SHE HEADS
OVER THE WESTERN PART OF THE
STATE.
SHE WILL HEAD THE TV MARKET IN
OMAHA OVER THERE.
ON FRIDAY, SHE'S HIT IOWA,
TELEVISION MARKET.
THE KAMALA HARRIS CAMPAIGN PLANS
TO HIT THE GROUND RUNNING AND
NOT LET UP.
THEY HAVE NOT RELEASE THEIR
TOTALS.
SHE JUMPED IN BEFORE ANYBODY
ELSE AND RAISING $12 MILLION IN
THAT FIRST QUARTER.
COMPARES TO MAYOR PETE BUTTIGIEG
AND JOE BIDEN WHO JUMPED INTO
THIS RACE LATER ON.
THIS IS ABOUT PAINTING CONTRASTS
AT THIS POINT.
KAMALA HARRIS SHOWS SHE WAS
WILLING TO DRAW CONTRASTS
BETWEEN HERSELF AND OTHER
CANDIDATES TAKE ON JOE BIDEN ON
THE ISSUE OF RACE AND BUSSING
AND ON THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
DEPORTATION AT THE DEBATE AND
THE QUESTION IS GOING FORWARD,
TO WHAT EXTENT WILL SHE CONTINUE
TO PRESS THE CASE SINCE THEY
PROSECUTED THE CASE AGAINST HER.
THAT STARTS HERE ON THE CAMPAIGN
TRAIL.
SHE'S GOT TWO EVENTS TODAY
BEFORE HEADING ON ACROSS IOWA.
SHE WILL BE IN NEW ORLEANS AND
ON SATURDAY, BEFORE GOING TO
SOUTH CAROLINA ON SUNDAY AND
MONDAY.
>> ALI.
>> WHAT IS THE CAMPAIGN DOING TO
BOOST MOMENTUM AND WHAT'S GOING
ON IN IOWA FOR SANDERS?
>> Reporter: WE HAVE SENATOR
SANDERS ABOUT TO OPEN UP THE
FIELD OFFICE HERE IN IOWA CITY.
IT IS AN EXAMPLE HOW THE
CAMPAIGN WANTS TO FOCUS ON WHAT
THEY CALL GROUND GAME.
AS WE POINT OUT THESE POLLS,
HE'S POINTING OUT SEVERAL MORE
SHOWING SANDERS CLOSING THE GAP
WITH BIDEN.
THAT'S WHY YOU HAVE SENATOR
SANDERS ON THIS TRIP GOING AND
PARTICIPAING IN THESE RETAIL
EVENTS.
HE'S DOING ICE CREAM SOCIALS AND
MARCHING IN 4th OF JULY PARADES
AND TRYING TO HAVE INTERACTIONS
WITH VOTERS.
RIGHT NOW THEY HAVE ABOUT 43
STAFFERS.
THE CAMPAIGN NOTES THAT'S LOWER
THAN SOME OF THE OTHER CAMPAIGNS
OUT THERE.
THEY HIGHLIGHT THEIR 25,000
VOLUNTEERS WHO STAFFERS ARE
GOING TO BE ABLE TO MOBILIZE AND
FOLKS ARE GOING TO KNOCK ON
DOORS AND MAKE CALLS.
THAT'S WHY EVENTS LIKE THIS ARE
HAPPENING.
THESE ARE RECRUITING EVENTS AND
HOPING TO PULL IN VOLUNTEERS AND
PEOPLE TO SUPPORT HIM COME THAT
CAUCUS.
>> THANKS THE THREE OF YOU, OUR
ROAD WARRIORS ON THE CAMPAIGN
TRAIL.
WE ARE LEARNING MORE OF THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IMMIGRATION
POLICIES WHICH MANY CRITICS SAY
CROSSES LINES OF ETHICS AND
HUMAN RIGHTS AND BASIC DEDECENC.
YOU ARE WATCHING "VELSHI &
RUHLE" LIVE ON MSNBC.
E" LIVE ONC
drive safely..
.
with Drivewise.
It lets you know when you go too
fast...
...and brake too hard.
With feedback to help you drive
safer.
Giving you the power to actually
lower your cost.
Unfortunately, it can't do
anything about that.
Now that you know the truth...
are you in Good Hands?
Let's get down to business.
The business of family time...
...and downtime.
...and you time.
...and forgetting what time it
is...altogether.
Modernized Comfort Inns
and Suites have been refreshed
because when your business
is making time,
our business is you.
Get the lowest price guaranteed
on all Choice hotels
when you book direct at
ChoiceHotels.com.
I switched to MiraLAX
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives
forcefully stimulate
the nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX works with
the water in your
body to unblock your
system naturally.
And it doesn't cause
bloating,
cramping, gas,
or sudden urgency.
MiraLAX.
Look for the pink cap.
Going to the Shawn Mendes
Verizon UP concert
was like an
out of body experience.
We were right in front of him.
Dead center. Front row.
'Cause actually, Zarmina,
you touched Shawn Mendes.
Yeah, I touched him!
She touched Shawn Mendes!
He like held my hand
for a while.
And then we got
to meet him after,
which was like...
Another surprise.
Yeah.
We love Verizon even more now.
I'll never forget
that day. Ever.
(VO)
The network more people rely on,
gives you more.
Like thousands of tickets
to concerts,
festivals and private shows.
And big savings on
our best phones when you switch.
You're turning onto the
street
That's Verizon.
when you barely
clip a passing car.
Minor accident
—no big deal, right?
Wrong. Your insurance
company is gonna raise
your rate after the other
car got a scratch so small
you coulda fixed
it with a pen.
Maybe you should take that
pen and use it to sign up
with a different
insurance company.
For drivers with Accident
Forgiveness, Liberty Mutual
won't raise their
rates because of
their first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
>>> THIS WEEK WE ARE GETTING A
BETTER UNDERSTANDING INSIDE
DETENTION CENTERS.
THE DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND
SECURITY'S OFFICE OF THE
INSPECTOR GENERAL TOUTED BORDER
FACILITIES AND RELEASED BLUNT
FINDINGS.
ABOUT 3,400 DETAINEES WERE HELD
LONGER THAN 72 HOURS.
THAT'S THE GUIDELINES FOR
MAXIMUM HOLDING TIME.
1500 OF THEM WERE HELD FOR MORE
THAN TEN DAYS AND 826 CHILDREN
HELD LONGER THAN 72 HOURS
LIMITS.
THAT REPRESENTS OF 31% OF THE
CHILDREN WHO WERE HELD OF CUSTOM
AND BORDER PATROL.
REASONABLE EFFORTS TO ALLOW
DETAINEES TO SHOWER WITHIN 72
HOURS TO BE MADE, SOME DULLS
WERE UNABLE TO SHOWER UP TO A
MONTH.
DETAINEES WERE GIVEN WET WIPES
FOR PERSONAL HYGIENE AND MANY
GOT SANDWICHES.
CHILDREN RECEIVING HOT MEALS
WERE NOT BEING MET.
DETAINEES WERE HELD IN OVER
CROWDED CELLS FOR UP TO A MONTH.
ONE MANAGER DESCRIBES THE
SITUATION AS "TICKING TIME
BOMB."
>> MANY VISITED THE FACILITY
INCLUDING ALEXANDER
OCASIO-CORTEZ TOOK TO TWITTER TO
REPORT ON THE CONDITIONS.
THEY REPORTED MIGRANTS WORKING
ODD HOURS FOR NO REASON.
AND A TEMPORARY RESTRAINING
ORDER QUOTED SEVERAL CHILDREN'S
INTERVIEW SAYING WE ARE IN A
METAL CAVE, I AM SO HUNGRY AND
LIGHTS ARE ON ALL THE TIME AND I
HAVE NEVER BEEN OFFERED TO
SHOWER.
GABE GUTIERREZ TALKED TO A
PEDIATRICIAN WHO TREATED SOME OF
THE CHILDREN.
HERE IS WHAT SHE HAD TO SAY.
>> CHILDREN SHOULD NOT BE IN A
PLACE WHERE THEY DON'T HAVE
ACCESS TO HUMAN BASIC NEEDS OR
IF THEY ARE SICK TO MEDICAL
PROVIDER.
IT IS DETRIMENTAL TO THEIR
HEALTH IN THE FUTURE.
>> JOINING ME IS JACOB SOBOROFF.
>> YES, THAT'S RIGHT, HE'S
CALLING ON THE OFFICE OF
PROFESSIONAL RESPONSIBILITY
WITHIN DHS TO INVESTIGATE, WHAT
THEY NORMALLY INVESTIGATE WHICH
IS MISCONDUCT AND A LACK OF
STANDARDS INSIDE THE APARTMENT
BEING HELD.
WHAT WAS EXTRAORDINARY SHOCKING
AND DEHUMANIZING LANGUAGE THAT
WAS BEING USED BY THE FOLKS THAT
WERE INSIDE THE GROUP AND A
GROUP OF LARGE AMOUNT OF PEOPLE,
I THINK 9500 PEOPLE BUT ULTIMATE
COME DOWN TO THE AX AND THE
LANGUAGE USED BY THE SPECIFIC
AGENTS IF INDEED THEY WERE
ACTING CURRENT BORDER PATROL
AGENTS AS THE TIME THEY USE
THOSE MESSAGES.
>> A LEGAL BATTLE OVER ASYLUM
SEEKERS, CAN YOU TELL US MORE
ABOUT THAT AND WHAT IT MEANS FOR
PEOPLE AT THE BORDER AND THESE
DETENTION FACILITIES?
>> ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR WANTED
TO HOLD ASYLUM SEEKERS IN
CUSTODY WITHOUT ANY ABILITY TO
BAIL THEMSELVES OUT.
FRANKLY HOLD THEM IN DETENTION
FOR DEPENDENCY FOR THEIR ASYLUM
HEARING.
ANOTHER ATTEMPT TO DETER
MIGRATION IN THE COUNTRY, IF YOU
COME HERE, TRY TO DETER ASYLUM,
WE'LL LOCK YOU UP.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT ASYLUMS,
NOT CRIMINALS.
THE JUDGE SIDED AGAINST ATTORNEY
BARR HERE IN THAT CASE.
ADMINISTRATION WILL NOT BE ABLE
TO LOCK PEOPLE UP ONLY BECAUSE
THEY WANT TO SEEK ASYLUM.
>> THE WASHINGTON POST REPORTED
OF A CHILD WHO DIED AFTER
SPENDING TIME IN CUSTODY.
WHAT DO WE KNOW FROM THIS FROM
THE AUTOPSY?
>> ULTIMATELY THIS CHILD DIED,
SEVERAL DISEASES AND PARASITES
AND WHAT THE LAWYER IS ALLEGING
NOW THAT THE AUTOPSY IS OUT,
THIS CHILD SHOULD HAVE GOTTEN
TREATMENT BEFORE HE AND HIS
MOTHER WERE SENT TO A HOSPITAL
ONCE THEY WERE DETAINED BY
CUSTOMS AND BORDER PROTECTION.
CPD WERE TAUTING FOR SOME TIME.
SINCE THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
BEGAN, SIX CHILDREN HAVE DIED IN
CUSTODY.
THIS IS MORE DETAILS OF ONE OF
THOSE CASES SPECIFICALLY AND IT
RAISES A LOT OF RED FLAGS ABOUT
WHY THESE CHILDREN ARE NOT
GETTING TREATMENTS SOONER.
WE SEE ALL OF THESE OVER
CROWDING CONDITIONS AND ALL
CONDITIONS OF CHILDREN LIKE THIS
ARE BEING HELD IN.
WHY ARE THEY NOT GETTING HELP
SOONER?
>> "THE DAILY BEAST" IS
REPORTING I.C.E. TOLD "HAPPY
HUNTING."
TELL ME ABOUT THAT.
>> "HAPPY HUNTING" SUPPOSED TO
HAPPEN BACK IN 2017.
THIS IS NOT AN ISOLATED USE OF
DEHUMANIZING PHRASE OF HAPPY
HUNTING.
OUR COLLEAGUE HAS ALSO REPORTED
THAT THE PHRASE HAPPY HUNTING
WAS USED BY BORDER PATROL
AGENTS, WE'LL BE DOING RANDOM
SPOT CHECKS ON GREYHOUND BUSES
AND OTHER MODES OF
TRANSPORTATIONS.
SEARCHES ON PUBLIC
TRANSPORTATION.
THE IDEA THAT WE'LL SEE IN
FACEBOOK REPORTS NOW OF
DEHUMANIZING LANGUAGE TOWARDS
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS AND
IMMIGRANTS AND U.S. GOVERNMENT,
I.C.E. AGENTS ARE SAYING HAPPY
HUNTING WHEN IT COMES TO
TRACKING DOWN.
AND BORDER PATROL AGENTS SAID
THE EXACT SAME THING AND THE
NORTHEAST OF THE UNITED STATES,
FAR FROM THE BORDER CERTAINLY
SUGGESTS THAT THERE IS A CULTURE
OF USING THIS TYPE OF LANGUAGE
WITHIN CPD AND WE HAVE NOT SEEN
A RESPONSE.
>> JACOB SOBOROFF, THANK YOU FOR
YOUR REPORTING IN LOS ANGELES.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
POLITICIZING THE NATIONAL 4th OF
JULY CELEBRATION.
WE'LL LOOK AT HIS PLANS AND THE
COST FOR THE FESTIVITIES.
YOU ARE WATCHING "VELSHI &
RUHLE," LIVE ON MSNBC.
WATCHING &
(birds chirping)
(KICKSTART MY HEART
BY MOTLEY CRUE)
(truck honks)
(wheels screeching)
(clapping)
(sound of can hitting
bag and bowl)
(clapping)
Always there in crunch time.
July Fourth lands on a Thursday
“I got it!”
So bookers are booking
a one, two, three,
that's a four day weekend
“Awesome”
And with getaway deals
on accommodation starting
from 15 percent off,
you can be a Booker
at Booking dot com
If you have moderate to
severe psoriasis,
on accommodation starting
from 15 percent off,
little things can be a big deal.
That's why there's Otezla.
Otezla is not a cream.
It's a pill that treats plaque
psoriasis differently.
With Otezla, 75% clearer
skin is achievable.
Don't use if you're
allergic to Otezla.
It may cause severe
diarrhea, nausea, or vomiting.
Otezla is associated with an
increased risk of depression.
Tell your doctor if you have a
history of depression
or suicidal thoughts
or if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor your
weight and may stop treatment.
Upper respiratory
tract infection
and headache may occur.
Tell your doctor about
your medicines
and if you're pregnant
or planning to be.
Ready to treat differently
with a pill?
Otezla. Show more of you.
♪♪
Did you know even the cleanest
looking cars can smell musty?
That's because odors trapped in
your car's soft surfaces
get released, and are then
circulated by your AC system.
To stop the cycle of odors
try Febreze CAR Vent Clips.
Febreze stops the circulation
of musty air
by trapping and eliminating
lingering odor molecules
for up to 30 days
of fresh, clean air.
Plus, they come in a range
of scents including extra light.
Stop the cycle of odors
in your car with
Febreze CAR Vent Clips.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "VELSHI &
RUHLE."
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS PREPARING HIS
"SALUTE TO AMERICA" EVENT.
IT IS A VERY DIFFERENT KIND OF
CELEBRATION THAN AMERICA IS USED
TO.
TANKS AND OTHERS WILL BE USED.
THE PRESIDENT'S EVENT WILL TAKE
PLACE AT THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL.
HE'LL GIVE REMARKS DESCRIBE AS
UPLIFTING AND PATRIOTIC BUT NOT
POLITICAL.
JOINING ME NOW, OUR
CORRESPONDENT KOURTNEY CUBY.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE LODGISTIC
OF THE MILITARY DISPLAY.
>> WE HAVE TO REMEMBER WE HAVE
SOMETHING LIKE AN ABRAMS TANK
THAT WEIGHS TONS AND TONS.
YOU CAN'T DRIVE IT DOWN THE
STREET.
IT IS NOT UNCOMMON FOR LARGE
MILITARY VEHICLES TO BE MOVED.
>> SO THAT'S WHAT THEY DID HERE.
THEY BROUGHT THESE TANKS UP FROM
GEORGIA, VIA RAIL AND THEY STUCK
THEM ON FLAT BEDS AND DROVE THEM
INTO THE CITY BECAUSE THEY WERE
SO CONCERNED OF THE WEIGHT BUT
ALSO THE TREADS.
THE TREADS CAN TEAR UP THE
STREETS.
THERE IS A LOT OF QUESTIONS OF
HOW ARE MILITARY LEADERS
REACTING TO THIS.
THERE IS WIDESPREAD CONCERNS OF
MILITARY OFFICIALS WE HAVE
SPOKEN TO SINCE THE IDEA OF THIS
PARADE CAME UP AND MAKING IT
DEDICATED TO THE MILITARY.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, THE
PENTAGON LAWYERS REVIEWED THE
PLAN AND THEY APPROVED IT.
THEY SAID THIS IS AN APPROPRIATE
THING FOR THE U.S. MILITARY TO
PARTICIPATE IN AND BE APART OF.
>> THE MILITARY HAD A PROBLEM
WITH IT, WOULD THEY BE COMPEL TO
THE SAME PEOPLE?
>> NO.
IF THEY HAD A PROBLEM AND IT WAS
CONSIDERED TO BE AN ILLEGAL  A
JUDGMENT THAT WOULD BE A
PROBLEM, BRINGING IN A POLITICAL
REALM THAT IN SOME WAY BE A
CONFLICT OF INTERESTS BEFORE
THEM.
IT IS NOT.
SO THE MILITARY IS
PARTICIPATING.
THERE IS SOME QUESTIONS ABOUT
WHY IS THAT SOME OF THE MORE
SENIOR MEMBERS OF THE JOINT
CHIEFS ARE NOT ATTENDING LIKE
ARMY CHIEF OF STAFF MARK MILLIE
OR GENERAL MILLER.
WELL, WE HAVE BEEN TOLD BY
NUMEROUS MILITARY OFFICIALS WE
HAVE BEEN ASKING ALL WEEK WHO'S
GOING TO BE ATTENDING.
THIS PARADE AND A LOT OF THESE
PEOPLE ALREADY HAVE PLANS.
SOME OF THEM PLAN TO BE OUT OF
TOWN OR BE ON LEAVE.
4th OF JULY IS NOT A TRADITIONAL
MILITARY HOLIDAY.
A LOT OF THESE GUYS PLAN TO TAKE
TIME OFF, ALI.
>> COURTNEY, THANK YOU FOR YOUR
REPORTING ON THIS.
JOINING US NOW, CONGRESSMAN
CISNERO.
HE'S A VETERAN HIMSELF.
GOOD TO SEE YOU, THANK YOU FOR
JOINING US.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>> AS YOU HEARD CONCERNS THAT
THE PRESIDENT'S 4th OF JULY
CELEBRATION IS HEAVY ON
PAGEANTRY AND COULD FEEL MORE OF
A CAMPAIGN TACTIC.
WHAT IS YOUR TAKE ON THIS?
THERE IS ALWAYS A PARADE.
THIS ONE SEEMS TO HAVE A BIT
MORE MILITARY COMPONENT AND A
BIT MORE --
>>> THE 4th OF JULY OF SHOULD BE
ABOUT CELEBRATING OUR DEMOCRACY
AND INDEPENDENCE.
WE HAVE VETERANS' DAY AND I
THINK RIGHT NOW WHAT HE'S DOING
IS TURNING THIS EVENT INTO A
SPECTACLE.
THAT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT WE
NEED.
A LOT OF THE GENERALS ARE NOT
GOING TO BE THERE BECAUSE THEY
MADE PLANS UNFORTUNATELY FOR
SERVICE MEMBERS THAT WILL HAVE
TO BE THERE WITH THE TANKS.
THEY HAVE TO BE THERE WITH THE
AIRCRAFTS FOR THE FLY OVER.
NOW THEY HAVE TO SPEND IT HERE
FOR THE PARADE INSTEAD OF
SPENDING WITH THEIR FAMILY AND
FRIENDS.
>> WE ARE HEARING THE DMZ DID
NOT GET ANY TICKETS TO THE
PRESIDENT'S EVENT.
WE HEARD KELLYANNE CONWAY SAYS
IT IS A PUBLIC EVENT.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS?
>> I KNOW I WAS NOT OFFERED ANY
TICKETS.
THIS IS WHAT THIS PRESIDENT IS
DOING.
HE'S TURNING IT INTO A CAMPAIGN
RALLY FOR HIMSELF AND THIS IS
NOT WHAT THE 4th OF JULY IS
SUPPOSED TO BE ABOUT.
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE
CELEBRATING THE BIRTH OF OUR
NATION, THE BIRTH OF OUR
DEMOCRACY AND REALLY HE'S
TURNING IT INTO AN EVENT
COMPLETELY FOR HIMSELF SOME
WHERE HE COULD HIGHLIGHT HIMSELF
AND WE'LL SEE SOME OF THESE
HIGHLIGHTS AND CAMPAIGN FOOTAGE
LATER ON.
>> WHAT IS YOUR SENSE OF
CONGRESS IS PLANNING TO TAKE
ACTION.
WE SAW THE INSPECTOR GENERAL'S
REPORT WHICH IS SCAVING AND GOES
RIGHT IN THE FACE OF WHAT DHS
OFFICIALS AND LEADERS OF THE
ADMINISTRATION HAVE BEEN SAYING
ABOUT THESE DETENTION CENTERS.
DHS REPORT IS RIGHT IN LINE OF
WHAT OUR REPORTERS AND WHAT YOU
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS HAVE BEEN
REPORTING ABOUT THESE CENTERS
AND INCOMPLETE CONTRAST OF WHAT
THE ADMINISTRATION IS SAYING.
>> WELL, THE DHS REPORT IS
CONFIRMING WHAT WE HAVE BEEN
HEARING ALL ALONG THAT THE
SITUATION DOWN THERE IN THE
FACILITIES IS ATROCIOUS.
YOU KNOW WE ARE TREATING THESE
INDIVIDUALS WHO ARE COMING HERE
TO THE COUNTRY JUST TRYING TO
SEEK A BETTER LIFE FOR
THEMSELVES AND FAMILIES.
WE ARE TREATING THEM WORSE THAN
OUR PRISONERS.
IT IS SOMETHING THAT NEEDS TO
CHANGE.
THAT'S WHY I COULD NOT SUPPORT
THE APPROPRIATIONS THAT PASSED
THROUGH THE HOUSE LAST WEEK THAT
THE PRESIDENT WAS GOING TO SIGN.
IT IS NOT GOING TO CHANGE ANY
POLICIES.
IT WILL BE BUSINESS AS USUAL FOR
HOMELAND SECURITY AND I.C.E.
WE NEED REAL ACTION THAT'S GOING
TO CHANGE THE CONDITIONS.
>> $400 MILLION, THAT CAN'T BE
BUSINESS AS USUAL.
>> A LOT OF IT IS GOING TO GO.
WE KNOW WHAT THEY ARE DOING.
THEY'RE SAYING THERE IS NOTHING
IN THAT BILL THAT'S GOING TO
CHANGE WHAT WAS GOING ON.
THERE IS NOTHING THAT'S GOING TO
CHANGE THE STANDARDS.
MAKE IT MANDATORY THAT THEY SEE
A POSITION.
WE ARE HEARING ABOUT THESE
CHILDREN WHO ARE DYING BECAUSE
NO ONE IS LOOKING AT THEM.
THEY HAVE THE FLU OR THINGS THAT
COULD BE TREATED SIMPLY THAT WE
HAVE THE MEDICATION TO DO AND
THEY ARE NOT GIVEN THAT
MEDICATION.
>> IT DOES NOT CHANGE POLICIES
BUT IT DOES FUND -- I GUESS I
WORRY OF WHAT YOU THINK OF A
GOOD HUMANITARIAN BILL THAT'S
NOT ACHIEVABLE AND VOTING
AGAINST ONE THAT'S ACHIEVABLE.
>> WELL, THIS IS A THING WE NEED
TO KEEP TO PUSH FOR IT AND I AM
GOING TO BE VOCAL ABOUT.
WE NEED TO PUSH FOR HUMANITARIAN
TREATMENTS OF THESE INDIVIDUALS
THAT ARE IN THESE FACILITIES.
WE NEED TO MAKE SURE THEY'LL
SEEK POSITIONS AND GET HOT MEALS
AND IT IS NOT A SANDWICH.
AGAIN, IT IS GOOD THAT THEY'LL
BE ABLE TO GET MORE BALOGNEY
SANDWICH.
WE NEED A BILL THAT WILL CHANGE
POLICIES AND MAKE SURE FAMILIES
ARE GETTING HOT MEALS AND
THEY'LL HAVE A TOOTHBRUSH AND BE
ABLE TO SHOWER THERE.
>> CONGRESSMAN CISNERO.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP LONG PROMISED
TO SLASH DRUG PRICES.
THOUSANDS OF DRUG PRICES HAVE
GONE UP DURING HIS
ADMINISTRATION.
WE'LL LOOK AT WHICH COMMON DRUGS
FROM SEEN THE BIGGEST HIKE.
YOU ARE WATCHING "VELSHI &
RUHLE," LIVE ON MSNBC.
E WATCHIN&
♪♪
As your life grows,
so do your needs.
♪♪
And with Bank of America
and Merrill,
the benefits you get
can grow, too.
As a Preferred Rewards member,
you can enjoy priority service
and exclusive discounts...
so your growing life
can be more rewarding, too.
♪♪
What would you like
the power to do?
♪♪
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS BEEN
PROMISING TO LOWER DRUG
PRESCRIPTION PRICES BUT IT
APPEARS SOME ARE SPIKING.
PRICE INCREASE BY 1.2% IN MAY
COMPARES TO THE SAME MONTH LAST
YEAR.
NEW ANALYSIS BY RX SAING
SOLUTIONS, IT IS A CONSULTANT
SHOWS THAT THE PRICE OF MORE
THAN 3400 DRUGS INCREASED ON AN
AVERAGE OF 17% COMPARES TO THE
SAME TIME LAST YEAR.
WHAT ELSE IS UP 17%?
THE AVERAGE PRICE HIKE IS 10.5%
OR ABOUT FIVE TIMES THE RATE OF
INFLATION OR YOUR PAYCHECK MAY
HAVE GONE UP.
AT LEAST 41 DRUGS INCREASED BY
MORE THAN 100%.
INCLUDES ONE VERSION OF
FLUOXETINE, UP 879%.
THIS IS A GENERIC.
MOMETASONE, INCREASED BY 800%.
AND COUGH MEDICINE WENT UP 300%.
20 COMPANIES RAISED THE LIST
PRICES OF MORE THAN 104
PRESCRIPTION DRUGS AN AVERAGE OF
13%.
ONE OF THEM IS A DRUG CALLED
ISOLYTE, IT IS A SALINE SOLUTION
USED TO HYDRATE PATIENTS IN
HOSPITAL FOR YEARS, ESSENTIALLY
SALT WATER.
WITH ME NOW, DR. JOHN TORRES,
EXPLAIN SOME OF THIS STUFF.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
I DWELL IN ECONOMICS AND YOU
DWELL IN MEDICINES.
I CAN NEVER FIGURE OUT HOW TO
MAKE SENSE OF THE INCREASES.
>> YOU ARE VERY WELL INFORMED.
YOU TRY TO PAY FOR IT AND YOU
FOUND OUT THE SAME DRUGS YOU
USED A YEAR AGO IS DOUBLED IN
PRICE AND YOU DON'T KNOW WHY.
THE WORD THAT YOU HEAR A LOT IS
TRANSPARENCY.
THAT'S THE BIGGEST PROBLEM THAT
WE HAVE HERE IS THOSE DRUG
PRICES ARE TRANSPARENT.
NOBODY KNOWS HOW THOSE PRICES
ARE SET AND HOW INSURANCE
COMPANIES DECIDE TO CHARGE.
WE HAVE THE MIDDLEMEN, THEY TAKE
THEIR CUT AS WELL AND SO THERE
IS A LOT OF HAND IN THAT PIE
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO GET
MONEY.
>> THEY'RE NEGOTIATING WITH DUG
MAKERS AND HEALTH PLANS AND
INSURANCE COMPANIES AND
PHARMACIES.
THAT'S SORT OF THE BLACK BOX.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENS
THERE.
>> THE MAGIC GOES ON IN THERE.
THE DRUG PRICE POPS OUT.
THAT DRUG PRICE CAN CHANGE FROM
MONTH TO MONTH.
>> DIFFERENT FOR YOU AND ME AND
SOMEONE PAYING CASH.
>> WHETHER YOU HAVE INSURANCE OR
NOT.
WHAT IT IS AND YOU CAME AT THE
SAME INSURANCE BUT HAVE
DIFFERENT CONTRACTS AND GETTING
CHARGED DIFFERENT AMOUNTS OF
MONEY.
>> WE ARE ABLE TO AND CRITICAL
OF THE ADMINISTRATION.
A LOT OF PEOPLE UNDERSTAND THIS
WORLD WHO SAYS PRESIDENT TRUMP
HAS BEEN TRYING TO MAKE PROGRESS
AND FELT IMPORTANT AND THAT HE'S
FRUSTRATED.
ALEX AZARE FOR NOT GETTING MORE
DONE.
WHAT DO WE KNOW WHAT'S GOING
ONTO BRING THESE DRUG PRICES
DOWN.
>> CAN YOU HELP LOWER YOUR
PRICES A LITTLE BIT?
MAYBE WE SHOULD MAKE SOME
REGULATIONS WHERE THEY ARE NOT
ABLE TO GET THAT PIECE OF THE
PIE THEY WANT TO GET.
THAT'S GOING TO LOWER PRICES AND
PHARMACIES AND DON'T DISTRIBUTE
IT FOR SUCH A BIG PRICE.
THERE ARE SO MANY DIFFERENT
ENTITIES INVOLVED IN THIS.
THEY HAVE A SYSTEM SET UP THAT'S
ALL TRANSPARENT.
EVERYBODY COMING AT THE BEGIN TO
DECIDE ONE.
AND TWO, WHAT'S THE PRICE WE ARE
GOING TO SET ON DRUGS.
AND IT IS JUST THE WAY THEIR
SYSTEM IS SET UP.
THAT'S ONLY BEEN FOR THE LAST
DECADES OR SO.
>> WE NEED SOMETHING IN THIS
COUNTRY.
THIS IS A GREAT DRUG SYSTEM FOR
PEOPLE WHO MAKE MONEY OFF OF IT.
IT IS VERY FRUSTRATING.
I WANT TO HEAR WHAT YOU THINK,
JOHN, THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR
BEING WITH US.
SEND ME AN E-MAIL OR TWEET ME
YOUR THOUGHTS ON WHAT YOU THINK
COULD BE DONE ABOUT DRUG PRICES
IN THIS COUNTRY.
>>> ANOTHER PIECE OF NEWS FOR
YOU.
VISIONARY LEE IACOCCA DIES ON
TUESDAY.
MANY OF YOU REMEMBER HIM AS
ENTERING THE AUTOMOBILE INDUSTRY
AS AN ENGINEER TRAINEE, THROUGH
A SERIES OF SUCCESSES AND THE
INVENTION OF THE MUSTANG,
IACOCCA BECAME THE PRESIDENT OF
FORD AT 46 YEARS OLD.
BECAUSE OF TENSIONS BETWEEN
HENRY FORD 2nd AND IACOCCA.
HE SAVED THE COMPANY FROM
BANKRUPTING BY INTRODUCING THE
FUEL EFFICIENT CAR LINE AND
ALLOWING THE COMPANY TO MAKE
SEVERAL DIFFERENT MODELS OF CARS
AT A TIME.
HE INTRODUCED MINIVANS AND
BRINGING CHRYSLER BACK INTO
COMPETITION.
HE MADE HIS NAME KNOWN BY
APPEARING IN COMMERCIALS.
HE WAS LISTED AS ONE OF THE
WORLD'S MOST RESPECTED MEN.
ONLY BEHIND RONALD REAGAN AND
POPE JOHN PAUL THE SECOND.
HE WAS 94 YEARS OLD.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
94 YEARS O.
Woman: (On phone) Discover.
Hi.
Do you have a travel card?
Yep. Our Miles card.
Earn unlimited 1.5 miles
and we'll match it at the
end of your first year.
Nice! I'm thinking about
a scuba diving trip.
Woman:
Ooh!
(Gasp)
Or not.
You okay?
Yeah, no, I'm good.
Earn miles. We'll match 'em
at the end of your first year.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "VELSHI &
RUHLE," THE REPORT DETAILS HOW
TECH ADVOCACY GROUPS ARE PUSHING
BACK AT LEGISLATION, AIMS AT
REGULATING MAJOR TECH GIANTS
WHICH WAS INTRODUCED BY JOSH
HOLLY LAST MONTH.
D.C. IS FEARING A QUOTE OF
PARTISAN BLOOD MATH.
ALAN SMITH IS JOINING US.
WHAT IS THIS ABOUT?
WHAT'S THE LARGER CONCERN?
>> SENATOR HOLLY, HE'S COMING IN
AND WANTING TO BE THE
REPUBLICAN.
HE'S THE FOREFRONT OF SOME OF
THESE TECH REGULATIONS BATTLE.
HE WANTS TO HAVE A MUCH MORE
ACTIVIST IN THIS REGARD.
THIS BILL THAT HE PROPOSED IS
VERY CONTROVERSIAL.
THE BILL WOULD REMOVE SOME OF
THE PROTECTIONS THAT MAJOR
COMPANIES ENJOY.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE FEEL THAT IT
IS A LITTLE OUT OF DATE.
>> A LITTLE BIT.
THIS LAW PROVIDES FREEDOM FOR
LIABILITY.
>> THE BACK PAGE IS THE BEST
EXAMPLE.
WE ARE A SITE THAT PEOPLE PUT
STUFF ON.
YOU
BACKPAGE ARGUES WE'RE JUST A
SITE.
YOU CAN'T HOLD US LIABLE FOR THE
CONTENT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WHAT HOLLEY CHOOSES TO DO, THE
FTC WOULD VOTE IF THE COMPANY'S
PRACTICES ARE, QUOTE,
POLITICALLY NEWT PRACTICE.
HOLLEY'S SIDE SAYS WITH A SUPER
MAJORITY HAVING TO GET ON BOARD
YOU WOULD HAVE A BIPARTISAN
RESPONSE.
THEY DON'T AGREE ON THE
DEFINITION RIGHT NOW AND SOME OF
THESE COMPANIES GET STUCK IN A
PURGATORY WHERE THEY'RE NOT
ACCEPTING IMMUNITY.
THEY'LL END UP WITH MUCH WIDER
SPREAD CENSORSHIP.
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO REVIEW
EVERY PIECE ON THE WEBSITE.
>> THANK YOU.
WE'RE SEEING RECORD CLOSINGS ON
ALL THREE MAJOR INDICES.
IN FACT, MARKETS CLOSED EARLY
BECAUSE TOMORROW IS THE JULY 4th
HOLIDAY.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT THREE NEW
RECORDS.
THE DOW AT 29966.
STANDARD & POOR'S, HALF A POINT
SHORT.
NASDAQ 8,170 POINTS.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT NIKE'S
CONTROVERSY.
A FLAG ON A SHOE.
WE'LL LOOK AT ALL SIDES OF THE
DEBATE AND NOW NIKE HANDLED THE
SITUATION.
YOU'RE WATCHING "VELSHI & RUHLE"
LIVE ON MSNBC.
♪
Corey is living with
metastatic breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking IBRANCE
with an aromatase inhibitor,
which is for postmenopausal
women
or for men with HR+ / HER2-
metastatic breast cancer
as the first hormonal
based therapy.
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease progression
versus letrozole.
Patients taking IBRANCE
can develop
low white blood cell counts,
which may cause
serious infections
that can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE, tell your
doctor if you have fever,
chills, or other signs
of infection,
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects include
low red blood cell
and low platelet counts,
infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth,
abnormalities in
liver blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash, and
loss of appetite.
Corey calls it her new normal
because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor
about IBRANCE.
The #1 prescribed FDA-approved
oral combination treatment
for HR+/HER2- MBC.
[ laughter throughout ]
♪ ♪
It's funny what happens
when people get together.
oral combination treatment
Holiday Inn.
Holiday Inn Express.
We're there.
So you can be too.
Going to the Shawn Mendes
Verizon UP concert
was like an
out of body experience.
We were right in front of him.
Dead center. Front row.
'Cause actually, Zarmina,
you touched Shawn Mendes.
Yeah, I touched him!
She touched Shawn Mendes!
He like held my hand
for a while.
And then we got
to meet him after,
which was like...
Another surprise.
Yeah.
We love Verizon even more now.
I'll never forget
that day. Ever.
(VO)
The network more people rely on,
gives you more.
Like thousands of tickets
to concerts,
festivals and private shows.
And big savings on
our best phones when you switch.
>>> TODAY, NIKE AND COLIN
KAEPERNICK ARE BACK IN THE
CENTER OF CONTROVERSY AND THIS
TIME IT'S OVER SNEAKERS.
NIKE IS PULLING THESE SHOES FROM
THE SO-CALLED BETSY ROSS VERSION
OF THE AMERICAN FLAG.
TO SOME PEOPLE THAT IS A FLAG
REPRESENTING HATE AND SLAVERY
BECAUSE IT WAS IN PLACE AT THE
TIME WHEN SLAVERY WAS ENSHRINED
IN THE UNITED STATES.
TO OTHERS, IT'S A PATRIOT SYMBOL
OF THE WAR.
STEPHANIE GOSK HAS MORE.
>> Reporter: NIKE'S RED, WHITE
AND BLUE WITH THE FLAG IS
WHIPPING UP EVEN MORE
CONTROVERSY, THREATENING TO PULL
THE MANUFACTURING PLANT IN HIS
STATE, ADDING WORDS CAN NOT
EXPRESS MY DISAPPOINT AT THIS
TERRIBLE DECISION.
THE FUTURE OF THE FACILITY WHICH
WOULD EMPLOY ABOUT 500 PEOPLE IS
UNCLEAR.
ACCORDING TO "THE WALL STREET
JOURNAL," FORMER NFL QUARTERBACK
COLIN KAEPERNICK SPEARHEADED THE
CALL TO GET NIKE TO PULL THE
SHOE.
CITING PEOPLE NAM WITH THE
MATTER, THE REPORT SAYS HE WAS
OFFENDED BY THE USE OF THE FLAG,
AS WERE OTHERS.
IN A STATEMENT, NIKE SAYS ITS
DECISION TO RECALL THE DESIGN
WAS BASED ON CONCERNS THAT IT
COULD UNINTENTIONALLY OFFEND AND
DETRACT FROM THE NATION'S
PATRIOTIC HOLIDAY.
WHEN THE ICONIC BRAND REVEALED
THE SHOE LATE LAST MONTH,
CRITICS SPOKE OUT.
ONE WRITING, NIKE, YOU SHOULD BE
ASHAMED OF THIS SHOE.
ANOTHER WROTE, CAN'T WAIT FOR
THE CONFEDERATE AIR MAX 90s.
THE SO-CALLED BETSY ROSS FLAG
NAMED AFTER THE 18th CENTURY
WOMAN KNOWN FOR DESIGNING IT.
SOME SAY IT CELEBRATES THE TIME
OF SLAVERY.
WHILE OTHERS INCLUDING TEXAS
SENATOR TED CRUZ ARE RENEWING
CALLING FOR A NIKE BOYCOTT.
CRUZ TWEETING IN PART THEIR
SHOES REPRESENT INSIDE DISDAIN
FOR THE AMERICAN FLAG.
SIMILAR CALLS WERE MADE WHEN
NIKE PARTNERED WITH KAEPERNICK
LAST YEAR IN AN AD CAMPAIGN.
>> BELIEVE IN SOMETHING.
EVEN IF IT MEANS SACRIFICING
EVERYTHING.
>> Reporter: THE FORMER
QUARTERBACK WAS THE FIRST IN THE
NFL TO KNEEL DURING THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM, PROTESTING POLICE
BRUTALITY AND RACIAL INJUSTICE.
SOME BURNED THEIR SHOES AND
BOYCOTTED NIKE, WHILE THE
COMPANY SAW ITS SALES RISE AND
ITS STOCK PRICE SURGE.
>> JOINING ME NOW IS NBC'S
STEPHANIE GOSK.
THIS WILL BE A CASE STUDY?
>> YES, AT THE MOMENT WHEN AT
THE CENTER OF A SNEAKERS WAR.
>> EVERYBODY HAS DUG INTO THIS
ONE.
>> YOU CAN MAKE AN ARGUMENT IT'S
A CONVERSATION WE KNEAD TO HAVE.
THERE ARE CLEARLY PEOPLE ON BOTH
SIDES WHO ARE AGITATED AND UPSET
FOR QUITE HONESTLY
UNDERSTANDABLE REASONS.
WHERE DO WE COME TOGETHER AS A
COUNTRY TO TALK ABOUT IT IS
REALLY THE CRUCIAL QUESTION.
>> I WAS SURPRISED IN YOUR PIECE
AND WHEN I LOOKED AT THE STORY
TO FIND THAT PEOPLE FOSHT THIS
SO-CALLED BETSY ROSS FLAG.
THEY MAY HAVE JUST CHANGED THE
STAR DESIGN WITH THE SAME
FEELINGS THAT PEOPLE HAVE FOR
THE CONFEDERATE FLAG.
>> RIGHT.
THERE HAVE BEEN LIMITED
EXAMPLES, FRINGES, THERE WAS A
CHAPTER OF THE KU KLUX KLAN THAT
HAD FLYERS IN UPSTATE NEW YORK
THAT USED THE FLAG TO RECRUIT
PEOPLE TO THEIR CHAPTER.
THAT'S OBVIOUSLY PRETTY LIMITED.
THERE WERE A COUPLE OF HIGH
SCHOOL STUDENTS AT A HIGH SCHOOL
FOOTBALL GAME A COUPLE YEARS AGO
THAT WERE WAVING THE FLAG AND
LATER THE SUPERINTENDENT CAME
OUT AND APOLOGIZED FOR THAT.
SAYING THAT THE FLAG HAD BECOME
WHAT HE CALLED A SYMBOL OF HATE
BUT THOSE ARE LIMITED EXAMPLES.
AND THIS CONTROVERSY, CLEARLY
THE MOST WIDESPREAD THAT WE'VE
SEEN WHEN IT COMES TO THIS FLAG.
>> THIS HASN'T REALLY HURT
NIKE'S STOCK PRICES.
NIKE HAS BEEN THROUGH
CONTROVERSIES.
BUT NIKE UNDERSTANDS BRANDING
POSSIBLY MORE THAN MOST OTHER
COMPANIES IN THE WORLD.
IS IT INTERESTING TO YOU THAT
THIS GOT TO THIS POINT WITHOUT
NIKE HAVING FIGURED OUT THERE
MIGHT BE SOME CONTROVERSY AROUND
THIS?
>> IT IS.
I ALSO THINK IT'S A STATEMENT ON
JUST HOW CONTROVERSIAL THIS FLAG
REALLY IS.
BECAUSE, LIKE YOU SAY, BRANDING
FOR NIKE IS SECOND NATURE.
THEY HAVE ALMOST DEFINED THE
BRAND FOR US.
>> YEAH.
WE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT THAT SWOOSH
WAS.
>> WITH THE MARKETING, YEAH.
AND SIGNING KAEPERNICK, YOU
KNOW, IN THOSE MOMENTS IN WHICH
THERE WAS A LOT OF CRITICISM
WHICH WILL THEY KNEW THEYE