I can't tell you who I am
or what I witnessed,
but I can tell you Liberty
Mutual customized my
car insurance so I only
pay for what I need.
Oh no, no, no, no,
no, no, no...
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
If you live with diabetes,
why fingerstick when
you can scan?
With the FreeStyle
Libre 14 day system
just scan the sensor
with your reader,
iPhone or Android and
manage your diabetes.
With the FreeStyle
Libre 14 day system,
a continuous
glucose monitor,
you can check your
glucose levels any time,
without fingersticks.
Ask your doctor to
write a prescription for the
FreeStyle Libre
14 day system.
You can do it
without fingersticks.
Learn more at FreeStyleLibre.us
♪♪
>>> IT WAS JULY 2017 WHEN DONALD
TRUMP, JUST MONTHS INTO HIS
PRESIDENCY, VISITED FRANCE ON
BASTILLE DAY.
HE ATTENDED A MILITARY PARADE.
HE WAS IMPRESSED.
THE MILITARY MIGHT, THE
SOLDIERS, THE TANKS.
HE WANTED HIS OWN PARADE.
TWO YEARS LATER, IT LOOKS LIKE
HE'S GETTING HIS WISH.
THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL IS BEING
PREPPED FOR A JULY 4th
SPECTACULAR, A POSSIBLE AIR
FORCE ONE FLYOVER, AND YOU
GUESSED IT, THANKS.
THERE'S NOT ONLY CONCERN ABOUT
POTENTIAL PARTISAN NATURE OF THE
PRESIDENT'S EVENT BUT THOSE
TANKS HAVE PROVEN TRICKY FOR THE
COMMANDER IN CHIEF.
HERE HE WAS YESTERDAY.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE SOME
TANKS STATIONED OUTSIDE.
GOT TO BE CAREFUL WITH THE TANKS
BECAUSE THE ROADS HAVE A
TENDENCY NOT TO LIKE HEAVY TANKS
SO WE HAVE TO PUT THEM IN
CERTAIN AREAS.
WE HAVE THE BRAND-NEW SHERMAN
TANKS, THE BRAND-NEW ABRAM
TANKS, AND WE HAVE SOME
INCREDIBLE EQUIPMENT, MILITARY
EQUIPMENT ON DISPLAY.
BRAND-NEW.
AND WE'RE VERY PROUD OF IT.
>> SO A COUPLE ISSUES HERE FOR
THE PRESIDENT.
ONE, SHERMAN TANKS HAVE NOT BEEN
IN ACTIVE SERVICE SINCE THE
1950s.
PROBLEM TWO, THE TANKS THAT ARE
COMING WEIGH ABOUT 60 TONS EACH,
AND THERE IS VERY REAL CONCERN
THEY COULD DO MAJOR DAMAGE TO
THE CAPITOL CITY STREETS,
BRIDGES AND, OF COURSE, OUR
COUNTRY'S FAMED NATIONAL MALL.
JOINING ME NOW, "WASHINGTON
POST" SENIOR NATIONAL AFFAIRS
CORRESPONDENT, JULIET AND MARK
JACOBSON.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK WITH MARK IN
A SECOND ABOUT THE TANKS, BUT,
FIRST, THE CONCERNS POTENTIALLY
HERE ABOUT PARTISANSHIP ON WHAT
IS TYPICALLY, YOU KNOW, A
PATRIOTIC HOLIDAY CELEBRATED BY
ALL AMERICANS.
KELLYANNE CONWAY THIS MORNING
INSISTED THAT IT WOULD BE
APOLITICAL.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> WHY IS THE REPUBLICAN
NATIONAL COMMITTEE GIVING OUT
TICKETS TO SUPPORTERS OF THE
PRESIDENT?
WHY ARE --
>> THIS IS A PUBLIC EVENT.
IT'S OPEN TO THE PUBLIC.
THE PUBLIC IS WELCOME TO COME
AND CELEBRATE OUR GREAT COUNTRY.
THE GREATEST DEMOCRACY.
THE CONSTITUTION, ALL THE
AMENDMENTS, NOT JUST THE FIRST
AMENDMENT THAT SEEMS TO ONLY
INTEREST YOU ONLY.
THE SECOND AMENDMENT, ALL THE
OTHERS.
BUT REALLY JUST THE BIRTH OF
THIS COUNTRY, THE GREATEST
DEMOCRACY THAT EVER LIVED.
I'M NOT GOING TO ALLOW YOU TO
POLITICIZE IT.
>> FAIR TO SAY THAT IT IS OPEN
TO THE PUBLIC.
HOWEVER, THERE IS THIS VIP
SECTION RIGHT UP FRONT WHERE,
YOU KNOW, TYPICALLY ANYONE WOULD
BE ABLE TO BE IN THAT AREA OF
THE MALL TO WATCH THE FIREWORKS
IF YOU GOT THERE EARLY ENOUGH.
NOW THE RNC HAS GOTTEN TICKETS
AND THE DNC TELLS PETER
ALEXANDER THEY HAVEN'T RECEIVED
AN ALLOTMENT OF TICKETS FOR THAT
AREA.
IT KIND OF UNDERMINES THIS
ARGUMENT.
>> SURE, THE FACT THERE'S
LIMITED VIP SEAT CHICAGO WE
REPORTED ON LAST WEEK SHOWS YOU
THAT, REALLY, THAT THERE ARE
SOME -- YOU KNOW, THERE ARE SOME
POLITICAL ELEMENTS.
NOW THE RNC, WE CHECKED WITH
THEM TODAY.
THEY'RE ARGUING IN THE SAME WAY
THAT, IF A DEMOCRAT WAS IN THE
WHITE HOUSE, THEY WOULD GIVE
TICKETS TO THEIR PARTY.
THAT THESE THINGS HAPPEN FOR
WHITE HOUSE HOLIDAY TOURS, FOR
THINGS LIKE THAT.
THAT'S ACCURATE, ALTHOUGH,
AGAIN, THOSE ARE WHERE YOU HAVE
LIMITS ON WHO CAN BE HERE.
THIS TRADITIONALLY HAS BEEN AN
ENTIRELY OPEN EVENT, AND IT'S
NOW BEING MODIFIED TO, YOU KNOW,
TO HAVE LIMITED ACCESS IN PART
OF THE MALL.
>> AND WE ARE, OF COURSE, GOING
TO GET A SPEECH FROM THE
PRESIDENT.
I MEAN, IT'S HARD TO ARGUE THAT
ANY SPEECH IN THIS KIND OF A
FORUM WOULD BE AN APOLITICAL
ONE.
>> WELL, ONE OF THE THINGS, IT
REALLY WILL MATTER WHAT HE SAYS,
WHETHER HE REFERS TO, FOR
EXAMPLE, ANY OF THE DEMOCRATS
CURRENTLY RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT
IN 2020.
WHETHER HE TALKS ABOUT POLLING.
THOSE ARE ALL COMMENTS THAT
COULD TRIGGER THIS PROVISION
WHERE UNDER FEDERAL
APPROPRIATIONS LAW YOU CAN'T USE
PUBLIC RESOURCES FOR POLITICAL
PURPOSES.
AND IF THEY DEEM THAT PART OF
THIS IS A POLITICAL SPEECH, THE
CAMPAIGN -- TRUMP'S PRESIDENTIAL
RE-ELECTION CAMPAIGN MIGHT HAVE
TO REIMBURSE THE U.S. TREASURY
FOR SOME OF THE EXPENSES OF THIS
EVENT.
>> SPEAKING OF THOSE EXPENSES,
MARK JACOBSON, THESE TANKS ARE
LOGISTICALLY DIFFICULT TO GET
HERE.
THIS IS ALSO GOING TO COST THE
U.S. MILITARY NOT AN INSIGIVE IN
-- INSIGNIFICANT AMOUNT OF
MONEY.
DOES THE MILITARY COMMUNITY KIND
OF AGREE HERE WITH THE PRESIDENT
THAT THIS IS A GOOD IDEA?
>> I SUSPECT THE MILITARY
COMMUNITY AND GOING BASED ON
CONVERSATIONS I'VE HAD WITH
THOSE ON ACTIVE DUTY AND
VETERANS, THERE'S A MIX OF --
MIXED VIEW ON THIS.
IF YOU LOOK AT THIS ENTIRE WEEK,
THIS SHOULD BE A BLIP COMPARED
TO ALL THE MISTAKES TRUMP SEEMS
TO HAVE MADE ON THE NATIONAL
SECURITY FRONT.
AT THE SAME TIME, YOU HAVE
NATIONAL PARK SERVICE THAT'S IN
DEBT ALREADY.
THERE'S A COST THEY CAN'T BEAR.
YOU HAVE A BUNCH OF TROOPS WHO
THOUGHT THEY WERE GOING TO SPEND
JULY 4th WITH THEIR FAMILIES WHO
NOR LONGER GOING TO SPEND JULY
4th WITH THEIR FAMILIES AND THIS
IS EXACTLY THE OPPOSITE OF WHAT
THE FOUNDING FATHERS MEANT IN
TERMS OF SYMBOLISM.
THE UNITED STATES WAS BORN OF A
FEAR OF A STANDING ARMY.
THE FOURTH OF JULY HAS NEVER
BEEN A MILITARY CELEBRATION.
IT'S A CELEBRATION OF POLITICAL
INDEPENDENCE AND THE IDEALS OF
THE ENLIGHTENMENT IN THIS
TRADITIONALLY AMERICAN WAY.
IT'S NOT SUPPOSED TO LOOK LIKE
NORTH KOREA OR THE SOVIET UNION.
AND THAT'S WHAT TRUMP SET UP
HERE.
>> THAT'S A GREAT POINT ABOUT
OUR FOUNDING FATHERS AND THE WAY
THEY ENVISIONED THIS HOLIDAY AND
WHAT FREEDOM AT THE TIME FROM
ENGLAND MEANT.
>> THERE'S A GREAT QUOTE WHERE
THE LATE HUMORIST TALKED ABOUT
FOURTH OF JULY IS ABOUT POTATO
SALAD AND HOT DOGS AND ISN'T IT
GREAT WE LIVE IN A COUNTRY WE
DON'T HAVE TO HAVE A PARADE WITH
GUNS AND TROOPS AND TANKS AND
THE PATRIOT -- TRUE PATRIOTISM
ON THIS DAY IS FEELING THAT --
LIKE YOU'VE EATEN TOO MUCH.
THAT'S FREEDOM.
>> JOHN McCAIN, THERE'S A
NONPROFIT ORGANIZATION THAT'S
GOING TO PRINT OUT SHIRTS THAT
FEATURE THE "USS JOHN McCAIN."
WHAT'S YOUR TAKE ON THE
SYMBOLISM OF THAT?
IT SEEMS AS THOUGH THE WHITE
HOUSE WANTS TO MAKE SURE THE
PEOPLE RIGHT IN FRONT OF THE
PRESIDENT ARE SUPPORTING HIM.
>> AS YOU'LL RECALL, THERE WAS
THIS "MISSION ACCOMPLISHED"
MOMENT DURING THE VISIT TO JAPAN
WHERE THE "USS JOHN McCAIN" WAS
SUPPOSEDLY GOING TO HAVE ITS
NAME HIDDEN AND ITS SAILORS
WEREN'T INVITED TO THE
PRESIDENTIAL ADDRESS.
I THINK THAT'S, AGAIN, A WAY OF
POKING BACK AT THE PRESIDENT.
AGAIN, IT'S A DAY WHERE WE
CELEBRATE OUR FREEDOMS,
INCLUDING FREEDOM OF SPEECH AND
EXPRESSION.
THE WHITE HOUSE SHOULD JUST HAVE
TRUMP GO GOLFING.
THAT'S WHAT PRESIDENTS ACTUALLY
DO ON JULY 4th.
THEY GO GOLF.
THIS WOULD BE A GREAT DAY TO DO
IT.
NOT TO GET INVOLVED.
SIT IN THE WHITE HOUSE, WHICH
USED TO HAVE A GREAT VIEW OF THE
FIREWORKS, AND LEAVE THIS A
CELEBRATION FOR THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE BY THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
>> THANK YOU GUYS SO MUCH FOR
YOUR PERSPECTIVES AND REPORTING
TODAY.
>>> COMING UP NEXT, HISPANIC
CAUCUS CHAIR JOAQUIN CASTRO
JOIN
S ME TO TALK ABOUT WHAT HE
WITNESSED DURING A TOUR OF A
BORDER FACILITY.
>> ONE OF THE WOMEN SAID THAT
SHE WAS TOLD BY AN AGENT TO
DRINK WATER OUT OF THE TOILET.
THESE ARE THE CONDITIONS --
THESE ARE THE CONDITIONS THAT
HAVE BEEN CREATED BY THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION.
THESE ARE THE INHUMANE
CONDITIONS THAT FOLKS ARE
FACING.
Let's get down to business.
The business of family time...
...and downtime.
...and you time.
...and forgetting what time it
is...altogether.
Modernized Comfort Inns
and Suites have been refreshed
because when your business
is making time,
our business is you.
Get the lowest price guaranteed
on all Choice hotels
when you book direct at
ChoiceHotels.com.
Here you go little guy.
A cockroach can survive
submerged
underwater for 30 minutes.
Wow.
Yeah.
Not getting in today.
Terminix. Defenders of Home.
Take Prilosec OTC and take
control of heartburn.
So you don't have to stash
antacids here...
Here...
or, here.
Kick your antacid habit with
Prilosec OTC.
One pill a day,
24 hours, zero heartburn.
♪ LiMu Emu ♪
And Doug.
What do all these people
have in common, LiMu?
[ guttural grunt ]
Exactly. Nothing!
They're completely
different people.
That's why they
make customized
car insurance
from Liberty Mutual.
They'll only pay
for what they need.
Yes, and they
could save a ton.
You've done it again, LiMu.
[ LiMu grunts ]
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty, Liberty,
Liberty, Liberty ♪
>>> AT THIS HOUR, NATIONWIDE
DEMONSTRATIONS ARE UNDER WAY
WITH PROTESTERS DEMANDING THE
CLOSURES OF DETENTION FACILITIES
HOLDING MIGRANT CHILDREN AND
FAMILIES.
ADVOCACY GROUPS ORGANIZED MORE
THAN 150 DEMONSTRATIONS, SOME
OUTSIDE OF CONGRESSIONAL
DISTRICT OFFICES, WHILE OTHERS
GATHERED OUTSIDE OF DETENTION
FACILITIES.
THE PROTESTS FOLLOW REPORTS OF
POOR CONDITIONS INSIDE SOME
MIGRANT DETENTION FACILITIES IN
TEXAS.
AND VISITS TO THOSE FACILITIES
BY DEMOCRATIC MEMBERS OF THE
CONGRESSIONAL HISPANIC CAUCUS
JUST YESTERDAY.
THIS AS CUSTOMS AND BORDER
PROTECTION HAS LAUNCHED AN
INVESTIGATION FOLLOWING A
PROPUBLICA REPORT EXPOSING A
SECRET FACEBOOK GROUP OF FORMER
AND CURRENT BORDER PATROL.
IN IT MEMBERS REPORTEDLY MOCKED
THE DEATH OF MIGRANTS AND POSTED
SEXIST MEMES.
NBC NEWS HAS NOT VERIFIED THE
FACEBOOK GROUP OR SEEN THE
POSTS.
JOINING ME NOW, MSNBC
CORRESPONDENT GABE GUTIERREZ.
YOU'RE IN EL PASO, I UNDERSTAND,
SPEAKING WITH PEDIATRICIANS THAT
HAVE TREATED MIGRANT CHILDREN
RELEASED FROM CUSTODY.
WHAT ARE THEY TELLING YOU ABOUT
HOW THESE KIDS ARE DOING?
>> HI THERE, KASIE.
WE'RE HERE OUTSIDE OF
ENUNCIATION HOUSE.
WE'VE BEEN COMING TO THIS
SHELTER FOR THE PAST YEAR OR SO
SINCE THE FAMILY SEPARATION
CRISIS OF LAST YEAR.
AND THEY DEAL WITH A LOT OF
MIGRANTS.
THEY TAKE IN A LOT OF MIGRANTS
THAT HAVE BEEN PROCESSED BY CBP
AND I.C.E.
THEY END UP IN THIS SHELTER
BEFORE THEY'RE SENT ALL OVER THE
COUNTRY AWAITING ASYLUM
PROCEEDINGS.
THEY'VE GONE FROM TAKING ABOUT
1,000 MIGRANTS A DAY NOW TO
ABOUT 100, 150.
WE'RE ALSO SPEAKING WITH SOME OF
THE PEDIATRICIANS TREATING THESE
CHILDREN, INCLUDING DR. LISA
RODRIGUEZ.
YOU'RE A LOCAL PEDIATRICIAN AND
YOU ARE TREAT SOMETHING OF THESE
CHILDREN, VERY YOUNG CHILDREN,
WHILE THEY'RE IN CBP CUSTODY AND
THEN AFTERWARD.
WHAT YOUR SEEING?
>> WE'VE HAD THE PRIVILEGE TO BE
ABLE TO TAKE CARE OF CHILDREN
WHO WHILE ARE IN CBP CUSTODY IF
THEY NEED TO BE HOSPITALIZED,
THEY GO TO THE HOSPITAL AND WE
CARE FOR THEM.
OR IF AFTER THEY ARE DISCHARGED
FROM CBP CUSTODY, IF THEY NEED
TO BE ADMITTED TO THE HOSPITAL,
WE TAKE CARE OF THEM AS WELL.
WE SEE A LOT OF COMMON CHILDHOOD
ILLNESSES IN THIS POPULATION.
A LOT OF UNFLUENZA, STOMACH
BUGS.
THE POPULATION IS UNIQUE IN THAT
THEY GET A LITTLE BIT SICKER
BECAUSE THEY'RE ALREADY A LITTLE
COMPROMISED.
THEY'RE DEHYDRATED.
THEIR NUTRITION ISN'T AS
EXPECTED.
SO THEY HAVE THE POTENTIAL TO BE
SICKER FASTER.
>> WHEN WE TOURED THE CLINT,
TEXAS, BORDER PATROL STATION
LAST WEEK, WE WEREN'T ALLOWED TO
TALK TO ANY CHILDREN.
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS HAVE BEEN
THERE AND TELLING STORIES OF
THEIR COMMUNICATION WITH THESE
CHILDREN.
WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD FROM
PARENTS, CHILDREN.
HAVE YOU HEARD ANYTHING THAT
TROUBLES YOU?
>> YEAH, I OFTEN TALK TO THE
FAMILIES WHO HAVE BEEN IN CBP
CUSTODY AND ASK THEM A LITTLE
BIT ABOUT WHAT THEIR TIME THERE
HAS BEEN LIKE.
MOST RECENTLY, I MET A YOUNG MOM
WHO HAD A NEWBORN BABY.
AND WHO WAS TALKING ABOUT THE
CHALLENGES OF KEEPING HER LITTLE
NEWBORN WARM.
SO THEY HAD GIVEN HER A PLASTIC
BLANKET AND THE BABY WAS IN A
ONESIE BUT SNUGGLE WITH THE BABY
AND I JUST COULDN'T KEEP THE
BABY WARM, DESPITE WHATEVER I
DID I COULDN'T KEEP MY BABY
WARM.
TALKED ABOUT THE HANDS AND FEET
BEING BLUE.
THAT'S JUST A SIMPLE, BASIC
HUMAN NEED THAT CONCERNED ME.
>> THANK YOU, DR. RODRIGUEZ.
BASED ON YOUR EXPERIENCE AND
YOUR OPINION, SHOULD CHILDREN
THIS YOUNG BE KEPT IN THESE
TYPES OF HOLDING FACILITIES?
>> NO CHILDREN SHOULD BE IN A
HOLDING FACILITY.
THEY NEED ACCESS TO THEIR BASIC
NEEDS.
IF THEIR CHILD IS SICK, THEY
NEED ACCESS TO MEDICAL CARE BY A
TRAINED PEDIATRIC PROFESSIONAL.
REALLY IT'S NOT A PLACE FOR ANY
KID TO BE.
>> THANK YOU, DOCTOR, FOR
SPEAKING WITH US.
THIS, THE ONGOING SITUATION DOWN
HERE ON THE BORDER.
EARLIER AT THE BORDER PATROL
STATION IN CLINT, TEXAS.
THAT CONTROVERSY FOLLOWING THE
PROPUBLICA REPORT.
THIS APPEARS TO BE A DEBATE WITH
NO END IN SIGHT.
>> ABSOLUTELY HEARTBREAKING TO
HEAR ABOUT AN INFANT SO COLD
THEIR HANDS AND FEET TURN BLUE.
>>> WHEN THE DELEGATION OF
DEMOCRATIC LAWMAKERS TOURED
THOSE MIGRANT DETENTION CENTERS
ALONG THE BORDER, THEY WERE TOLD
TO SURRENDER THEIR DEVICES
BEFORE THEY'D BE ALLOWED TO
ENTER THE FACILITIES.
BUT CONGRESSMAN JOAQUIN CASTRO
OF TEXAS WAS ABLE TO SNEAK A
PHONE IN WITH THE CONSENT OF THE
WOMEN IN CUSTODY, CASTRO FILMED
THEIR SMALL CELL WHICH INCLUDED
A TOILET BUT NO RUNNING WATER.
HE POSTED THE IMAGES ON TWITTER
SAYING MANY SAID THEY HAD NOT
BATHED FOR 15 DAYS.
SOME HAD BEEN SEPARATED FROM
CHILDREN.
SOME HAD BEEN HELD FOR MORE THAN
50 DAYS.
SEVERAL COMPLAINED THEY HAD NOT
RECEIVED THEIR MEDICATION.
JOINING ME NOW, TEXAS DEMOCRATIC
CONGRESSMAN JOAQUIN CASTRO.
IS THE CHAIRMAN OF THE OF THE
CONGRESSIONAL HISPANIC CAUCUS.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE TODAY.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> I WANT TO START WITH THE
BASICS HERE.
I THINK IT'S HARD FOR A LOT OF
AMERICANS TO WRAP THEIR HEADS
AROUND THE IDEA THAT YOU AS
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS, REGARDLESS
OF WHAT PARTY YOU MAY BELONG TO
AREN'T ABLE TO GO INTO
FACILITIES OUR GOVERNMENT IS
PAYING FOR AND ACTUALLY DOCUMENT
WHAT YOU SEE.
WHAT DID IT TAKE FOR YOU TO GET
YOUR PHONE INTO THIS FACILITY SO
THAT THOSE IMAGES COULD GET OUT
THERE?
>> I JUST KEPT IT IN MY POCKET
WHEN THEY TOLD US TO PUT IT ON
THE TABLE.
WE ASKED THEM REPEATEDLY.
WE CHALLENGED THEM AND ASKED
THEM WHAT LAW ALLOWS THEM TO
FORCE US TO KEEP OUR PHONES AND
CAMERAS AWAY FROM THE FACILITY.
AND THE BORDER PATROL CHIEF
THERE COULDN'T GIVE US AN
ANSWER.
THERE WAS A LAWYER THERE AND SHE
COULDN'T GIVE US AN ANSWER.
AND SO AT THAT POINT, AS FAR AS
I'M CONCERNED, THEY HAVE NO
RIGHT TO TRY TO KEEP LEGISLATORS
WHO ARE ENTRUSTED WITH OVERSIGHT
OF THEIR AGENCY FROM DOCUMENTING
WHAT THEY SEE.
PARTICULARLY, GIVEN WHAT'S AT
STAKE AND GIVEN WHAT'S GOING ON
RIGHT NOW.
>> SO WHAT IN YOUR VIEW COULD
POSSIBLY BE THE EXPLANATION?
I THINK IT STRIKES A LOT OF
PEOPLE THAT THEY SIMPLY DON'T
WANT ANYONE TO FIND OUT WHAT IS
ACTUALLY GOING ON.
>> AND I THINK THAT THAT'S
RIGHT.
I THINK THEY'RE SCARED.
I THINK THAT THE REASON THINGS
DON'T CHANGE THE WAY THEY SHOULD
IS BECAUSE THESE THINGS ARE KEPT
SECRET.
FOR EXAMPLE, THERE WAS A POINT
AT WHICH WE WERE IN ONE OF THE
TENTS THAT WAS EMPTY.
THEY'D ALREADY MOVED EVERYBODY
OUT.
THESE ARE DARK TENTS WITH CHAIN
LINK FENCES.
WHEN THE SURGE HAPPENED, THEY
HAD, YOU KNOW, MAYBE 100, 200
PEOPLE IN THERE.
AND THEY HAD SAID YOU CAN'T TAKE
PICTURES BECAUSE YOU CAN'T
VIOLATE THE PRIVACY OF THESE
CHILDREN.
AND SO WE SAID, OKAY.
WELL, THIS TENT IS EMPTY.
THERE'S NOBODY IN HERE.
CAN WE TAKE A PHOTO OF THE TENT.
THEY SAID, NO.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
THEY'RE TRYING TO KEEP
EVERYTHING SECRET.
>> SO THEY ARE, OF COURSE,
PUSHING BACK ON SOME OF THE
CLAIMS YOU HAVE HEARD FROM THESE
WOMEN THAT YOU SHOW IN YOUR
VIDEO AND FROM OTHERS THAT YOU
SPOKE TO.
DO YOU HAVE ANY REASON NOT TO
BELIEVE WHAT THESE MIGRANT
DETAINEES TOLD YOU?
>> I DON'T.
THEY SPOKE SINCERELY.
THERE WAS A POINT WHERE ONE OF
THE WOMEN WHO WAS CUBAN, SHE
SPOKE SOME ENGLISH.
AND IN FRONT OF ALL OF US, MANY
OF THE LEGISLATORS AND ALSO
SEVERAL CBP OFFICERS, SHE
CHALLENGED THEM VERY DIRECTLY
AND SAID THAT THEY WERE NOT
TELLING THE TRUTH ABOUT THE
STANDARD OF CARE AND THE
TREATMENT.
AND SHE SAID THAT SOME OF THE
AGENTS HAD USED DEROGATORY
WORDS, LANGUAGE AGAINST THE
WOMEN.
NOW I'M NOT SAYING THAT SHE SAID
THAT ALL OF THE AGENTS DID THAT.
BUT SHE SAID THAT IT SOUNDED TO
ME LIKE A FEW OF THEM HAD.
SO SHE VERY DIRECTLY CHALLENGED
THEM IN FRONT OF ALL OF US.
AND THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS
THESE WOMEN WERE SCARED OF
RETRIBUTION.
BUT IF THERE'S A DISPUTE ABOUT
WHAT THE TRUTH IS IN THOSE
FACILITIES, THEN I THINK THERE'S
A VERY EASY WAY TO SOLVE THAT.
THEY HAVE CAMERAS UP IN ALL OF
THOSE ROOMS.
THEY CAN SIMPLY PUT OUT THE
VIDEO FROM ALL THOSE CAMERAS AND
THEY CAN LET THE PRESS DO THEIR
JOBS AND GO INSIDE THERE AND THE
PRESS CAN BE THE TIEBREAKER
ABOUT WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> SO THE GOVERNMENT HAS FOOTAGE
OF WHAT'S GONE ON IN THESE
FACILITIES?
THEY'VE BEEN VIDEOTAPING?
ALL OF THIS IS ON CAMERA AND YET
WE AS THE AMERICAN PUBLIC JUST
CAN'T SEE IT?
>> YEAH, LOOK, THEY KNEW I WAS
TAKING A PICTURE OF THOSE FOLKS.
THEY KNEW THAT I PULLED MY
CAMERA OUT.
I'M SURE SOMEBODY WAS WATCHING
ME IN THAT ROOM.
I SAW THE OVERHEAD CAMERA RIGHT
THERE.
THERE WERE PROBABLY FIVE AGENTS
THAT WERE WATCHING THAT.
SO THEY HAVE FOOTAGE OF ALL OF
THAT.
>> SO TO PICK UP ON ANOTHER
POINT THAT YOU WERE MAKING.
YOU SAID IN THIS FACILITY, THERE
WERE BORDER PATROL AGENTS OR
PERSONNEL THAT HAD BEEN ACCUSED
OF BEHAVING, FRANKLY IN A WAY
THAT'S NOT BECOMING OF PEOPLE
WHO WEAR A UNIFORM IN THE UNITED
STATES, OF THE UNITED STATES.
THERE'S ALSO BEEN PROPUBLICA
REPORTING ON A SECRET FACEBOOK
GROUP THAT MANY BORDER PATROL
AGENTS AND FORMER AGENTS ARE A
MEMBER OF WHERE THEY HAVE SAID
SOME DESPICABLE THINGS,
ALLEGEDLY, AND THAT THERE'S NOW
AN INVESTIGATION GOING ON.
WHAT SHOULD HAPPEN TO THE PEOPLE
WHO ARE FOUND TO HAVE BEEN -- BE
MAKING THESE TYPE OF COMMENTS
AND BE TREATING PEOPLE THIS WAY?
>> WELL, THE PEOPLE THAT MADE
THOSE VERY DIRECT COMMENTS ABOUT
SOME OF THE MEMBERS OF CONGRESS,
ABOUT SOME OF THE PEOPLE THAT
WERE ENTRUSTED IN THEIR CARE,
THEY ARE DESENSITIZED TO THE
POINT OF BEING DANGEROUS TO THE
MIGRANTS AND ALSO TO THEIR
CO-WORKERS.
AND THEY NEED TO BE RELIEVED OF
DUTY.
THEY REALLY SHOULD NOT BE
WEARING ANY UNIFORM THAT
REPRESENTS THE UNITED STATES OF
AMERICA.
AND ALSO, THE AGENTS THAT WERE
ON THERE THAT DID NOT TURN THOSE
PEOPLE IN NEED TO BE DEALT WITH
AND HELD ACCOUNTABLE IN SOME WAY
ALSO.
>> DO YOU TAKE ANY ISSUE WITH
HOW YOUR DEMOCRATIC LEADERS IN
CONGRESS HANDLED THE RECENT
FUNDING BILL TO TRY AND HELP
ALLEVIATE THIS CRISIS?
THE MONEY THAT ULTIMATELY IS
GOING TO BE SPENT AS PART OF
THAT BILL DOESN'T HAVE SOME OF
THE RESTRICTIONS THAT DEMOCRATS
WANTED.
MANY PROGRESSIVES WERE VERY
ANGRY ABOUT HOW THAT ALL PLAYED
OUT.
DO YOU FEEL AS THOUGH YOUR
LEADERSHIP ACTED IN BAD FAITH,
AND ARE YOU GIVING -- DID
CONGRESS GIVE TOO MUCH TO THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION AS THEY
CLAIM THAT THEY'RE TRYING TO
DEAL WITH THIS?
>> WELL, I THINK THEY MOSTLY RAN
UP AGAINST A BUZZSHAW OF MITCH
McCONNELL AND PRESIDENT TRUMP
WHO DON'T CARE VERY MUCH FOR THE
PEOPLE IN THOSE DETENTION
CENTERS.
THERE'S NO QUESTION THAT WE
NEEDED STRONGER SAFEGUARDS OR
GUARDRAILS AROUND THAT MONEY SO
THAT IT CAN'T BE TRANSFERRED OUT
AND AWAY FROM HUMANITARIAN AID.
AND ALSO, WE ALSO NEEDED NOT
JUST TO PUMP A BUNCH MORE CASH
INTO THESE FACILITIES.
FOR EXAMPLE, WHEN WE PASSED
THROUGH SOME OF THE WALKWAYS, WE
SAW STACKS OF GRANOLA BARS.
I LOOKED AT ANOTHER CELL AND
THERE WAS A FAMILY EATING RAMEN
HUDDLED ON THE FLOOR EATING
RAMEN NOODLES.
IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT MORE CASH
FOR THEM TO BUY RAMEN NOODLES
AND GRANOLA BARS.
YOU HAVE TO CHANGE THE MEDICAL
STANDARDS AND ALSO THE STANDARDS
OF CARE AND TREATMENT.
AND UNFORTUNATELY IN THAT SENATE
BILL THAT FINALLY PASSED, THERE
ISN'T ENOUGH OF THAT.
WE NEED TO DO A BETTER JOB.
>> TEXAS CONGRESSMAN JOAQUIN
CASTRO, THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR
YOUR TIME TODAY.
I APPRECIATE IT.
>>> COMING UP NEXT -- THE
PRESIDENT'S QUEST TO NOT BE
FORGOTTEN.
N.
the worst...
...especially when your easily
distracted teenager has the car.
At Subaru, we're taking on
distracted driving
[PING]
with sensors that alert you when
your eyes are off the road.
The all-new Subaru Forester.
The safest Forester ever.
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. Healthier Brain.
Better Life.
♪
Corey is living with
metastatic breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking IBRANCE
with an aromatase inhibitor,
which is for postmenopausal
women
or for men with HR+ / HER2-
metastatic breast cancer
as the first hormonal
based therapy.
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease progression
versus letrozole.
Patients taking IBRANCE
can develop
low white blood cell counts,
which may cause
serious infections
that can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE, tell your
doctor if you have fever,
chills, or other signs
of infection,
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects include
low red blood cell
and low platelet counts,
infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth,
abnormalities in
liver blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash, and
loss of appetite.
Corey calls it her new normal
because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor
about IBRANCE.
The #1 prescribed FDA-approved
oral combination treatment
for HR+/HER2- MBC.
>>> IF THERE'S ONE THING THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP DOES
CONSISTENTLY, IT'S PROVIDE
COMPLIMENTS.
USUALLY TO HIMSELF.
HE WAS, AS HE WAS IN A RECENT
INTERVIEW WITH FOX NEWS' TUCKER
CARLSON.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE GAVE ME A LOT
OF CREDIT.
>> THE PUBLIC WAS ON YOUR SIDE,
IF SURE.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE SAID THAT WAS
A GREAT PRESIDENTIAL MOMENT.
I WON.
THEY WERE TOTALLY AGAINST ME.
I HAVE MILLIONS AND MILLIONS OF
PEOPLE ON TWITTER.
A POLL CAME OUT TODAY.
I'M AT 54, 55 AND THEY SAY YOU
CAN ADD 10 TO WHATEVER POLL I
HAVE.
AND YET I WON.
AND I WON AGAIN.
>> THEY DO?
>> THAT WAS TAPED DURING TRUMP'S
TRIP TO ASIA WHEN HE BECAME THE
FIRST SITTING MOMENT TO STEP
INTO NORTH KOREA.
THE PRESIDENT ALREADY THINKS
THAT IT DID.
HE TOLD REPORTERS HIS PRESIDENCY
WAS, QUOTE, THE HOTTEST SHOW IN
TOWN.
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" PETER BAKER
WROTE ABOUT THE PRESIDENT'S
QUEST FOR SUPERLATIVES SAYING
WHATEVER HE IS DOING MUST BE THE
FIRST, THE MOST, THE BIGGEST,
AND IT SHAPES HIS POLICY CHOICES
EVEN AS HE FRAMES HIS OWN
NARRATIVE WITH THE BRANDING
SKILLS OF A CAREER IN BUSINESS
AND ENTERTAINMENT.
JOINING ME IS MSNBC POLITICAL
ANALYST PETER BAKER.
PETER, I JUST SAW YOUR TWEET A
COUPLE MINUTES BEFORE WE CAME ON
THE AIR THAT IN THE COURSE OF
ONE NEWS CONFERENCE, THE
PRESIDENT USED BEST NINE TIMES,
INCREDIBLE 16 TIMES, TREMENDOUS
28 TIMES AND GREAT OR GREATEST
50 TIMES.
KUDOS WHO WHOEVER WENT THROUGH
AND COUNTED UP ALL OF THOSE
WORDS.
WITH THE REALITY HERE, SOMETIMES
HE'LL MAKE STATEMENTS THAT ARE
SIMPLY NOT TRUE IN THE INTEREST
OF TAKING -- YOU KNOW,
PRESENTING HIMSELF IN THE WAY
THAT YOU WRITE ABOUT.
>> YEAH, LOOK.
THIS IS A SALESMAN.
THIS IS WHAT HIS HISTORY IS.
HE'S AN ENTERTAINER, AND I THINK
HE UNDERSTANDS THAT REPETITION
AND SELLING -- UP SELLING IN
EFFECT WORKS.
AND IF THE FACTS ARE
INCONVENIENT OR GET IN THE WAY
YOU JUST EITHER IGNORE THEM OR
REWRITE THEM.
AND IN THIS CASE, HE HAS THE
BEST ECONOMY EVER.
HE HAS THE STRONGEST PRESIDENT
EVER, THE BEST NEGOTIATION EVER.
THE BEST DEAL EVER.
AND THIS HAS AN IMPACT.
IT DOES, IN FACT, CREATE A
NARRATIVE OUT THERE THAT A LOT
OF PEOPLE APPRECIATE AND
UNDERSTAND AND AGREE WITH EVEN
IF OTHERS ARE SORT OF SPINNING
MAD BECAUSE HE'S KIND OF PLAYING
FAST AND LOOSE WITH THE FACTS.
YOU KNOW, HE CLEARLY WANTS TO BE
IN THE HISTORY BOOKS.
THIS IS ONE OF THE REASONS WHY
HE GOES TO THE DMZ AND WALKS
ACROSS THAT LINE INTO NORTH
KOREA BECAUSE HE WAS TOLD NO
OTHER PRESIDENT HAD DONE IT
BEFORE.
IT'S A FIRST.
HE LIKES TO BE SOMEONE WHO HAS
DONE THE FIRST.
BROKEN A BARRIER AND DONE
SOMETHING THAT NO ONE ELSE HAS
DONE.
THE QUESTION IS YOU JUST PUT IT
CORRECTLY, DOES THIS MEAN
SOMETHING MORE ENDURING?
AND THAT'S THE UNANSWERED
QUESTION.
>> AND IN THAT INTERVIEW WITH
TUCKER CARLSON, PETER, FIRST OF
ALL, I THINK PEOPLE THOUGHT IT
WAS INTERESTING, SHALL WE SAY,
THAT CARLSON WAS ON THE TRIP,
ACTING AS A DE FACTO FOREIGN
POLICY ADVISER WHILE HIS OWN
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER WAS
OFF IN MONGOLIA.
BUT SETTING THAT ASIDE, THERE
WERE SOME INTERESTING --
INTERESTING, SHALL WE SAY,
ANSWERS TO SOME OF THE QUESTIONS
CARLSON POSED.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU HIS ANSWER ON
HOMELESSNESS SPECIFICALLY AND
THEN WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
>> IN NEW YORK CITY, SAN
FRANCISCO, LOS ANGELES, THEY'VE
GOT A MAJOR PROBLEM WITH --
>> IT'S VERY SAD.
>> WITH FILTH.
>> WHY IS THAT?
>> IT'S A PHENOMENA THAT STARTED
TWO YEARS AGO.
IT'S DISGRACEFUL.
I AM GOING TO MAYBE -- AND I'M
LOOKING TAT VERY SERIOUSLY.
YOU KNOW, I HAD A SITUATION WHEN
I FIRST BECAME PRESIDENT.
WE HAD CERTAIN AREAS OF
WASHINGTON, D.C., WHERE THAT WAS
STARTING TO HAPPEN, AND I ENDED
IT QUICKLY.
WHEN WE HAVE LEADERS OF THE
WORLD COMING IN TO SEE THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
AND THEY CAN'T BE LOOKING AT
THAT.
I REALLY BELIEVE THAT IT HURTS
OUR COUNTRY.
>> SO, PETER, NOT ONLY IS HE
SAYING IN ANOTHER EXAMPLE OF
THIS PHENOMENON WHERE HE SOLVED
SOME OF THE PROBLEMS.
HE REMOVED HOMELESS PEOPLE SO
OTHER LEADERS WOULDN'T SEE THEM.
BUT ALSO SAID THIS IS A
PHENOMENON THAT ONLY STARTED TWO
YEARS AGO.
WHERE DID THAT COME FROM?
>> YEAH, WE WERE TRYING TO
FIGURE THAT OUT TODAY.
WE'VE BEEN SCOURING, YOU KNOW,
FOX AND SOME OF THE OTHER PLACES
HE GETS HIS INFORMATION FROM TO
SEE IF HE'S REACTING TO
SOMETHING SPECIFIC.
AND IT'S HARD TO UNDERSTAND
EXACTLY.
OBVIOUSLY, HOMELESSNESS DID NOT
JUST START TWO YEARS AGO.
NO QUESTION THERE'S BEEN, YOU
KNOW, AN UP TICK IN SOME PLACES.
IN FACT, CALIFORNIA HAS BEEN
DEALING WITH THIS.
IT'S BEEN A BIG ISSUE IN THE
LAST FEW WEEKS IN LOS ANGELES IN
PARTICULAR.
HE, OF COURSE, YOU KNOW, BUT HE
SEES IT NOT AS A HUMANITARIAN
ISSUE THE WAY HE FRAMES IT IN
THAT INTERVIEW AS WELL.
IT'S A PUBLIC RELATIONS ISSUE.
IT'S AN ISSUE YOU DON'T WANT
WORLD LEADERS TO SEE AND,
THEREFORE, YOU WANT TO GET THESE
PEOPLE OUT OF THE WAY.
NOT TO MAKE SURE THEY'RE GETTING
CARE OR TO GET THEM INTO HOMES,
BUT TO MAKE SURE THEY'RE NOT
VISIBLE FOR VISITING LEADERS.
THAT'S A STRIKING FRAMEWORK ON
HIS PART.
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT HE'S
TALKING ABOUT.
HE SAID TWO YEARS AGO THERE WAS
AN ISSUE AND HE SNAPS HIS FINGER
AND SUDDENLY IT'S GONE.
I LIVE IN WASHINGTON.
IT'S HARD TO KNOW WHAT HE'S
TALKING ABOUT BECAUSE
HOMELESSNESS HAS BEEN AN ISSUE
HERE FOR A LONG TIME.
HASN'T CHANGED SPECIFICALLY IN
THE LAST TWO YEARS IN A
MEANINGFUL WAY.
>> IF ANYTHING, IT'S GOTTEN TO
BE ONE OF OUR MORE VISIBLE
PROBLEMS.
PETER BAKER, THANK YOU.
ALSO, THANK YOU FOR THE WESTERN
LIBERALISM QUESTION DURING THE
NEWS CONFERENCE.
WE WERE ALL A LITTLE TAKEN ABACK
BY THE PRESIDENT'S
INTERPRETATION OF YOUR QUESTION,
BUT THANK YOU FOR ASKING IT.
AND THANKS FOR BEING HERE TODAY.
>>> COMING UP NEXT -- AS THE
FIELD OF DEMOCRATIC PRESIDENTIAL
CANDIDATES PREPARE FOR THE NEXT
DEBATE, CLIMATE CHANGE REMAINS A
TOP ISSUE AMONG PRIMARY VOTERS.
BUT HOW DOES THE COUNTRY BALANCE
CONCERNS OVER THE ENVIRONMENT
WITH THE NEED FOR JOBS AND
REVENUE FROM INDUSTRIES LIKE
COAL?
NBC'S CAL PERRY TRAVELED TO
MONTANA TO FIND OUT.
CAL, THIS IS REALLY THE CENTRAL
QUESTION AS WE KIND OF TRY TO
GRAPPLE WITH THIS AS A COUNTRY
AND AS WE FRANKLY FAIL TO
GRAPPLE WITH THIS AS A COUNTRY.
THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE WHO
DEPEND ON THESE OLD INDUSTRIES
FOR THEIR LIVELIHOODS AND MAKING
THAT TRANSITION IS INCREDIBLY
DIFFICULT.
YOU TALKED TO ONE CANDIDATE WHO
DIDN'T MAKE THE DEBATE STAGE
ABOUT ALL OF THIS.
>> YOU'RE NAILING THE ISSUE.
IT'S A DIFFICULT BALANCE
ESPECIALLY IN A PLACE LIKE
MONTANA.
WE WENT OUT THERE.
SPENT TIME WITH THE GOVERNOR,
GOVERNOR BULLOCK.
HE'S TRYING TO DO THAT, WALK
THAT FINE LINE IN AN INDUSTRY
AND STATE THAT STILL RELIES ON
FOSSIL FUELS.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> I'M JUST ABSOLUTELY AMAZED AT
THE BIG OPEN SKIES.
>> EVERYTHING THAT WE'RE SEEING
AROUND US IS JUST ABSOLUTELY
BEAUTIFULLY CARVED.
>> ONE OF THE REASONS I WANTED
TO COME HERE WAS JUST ENJOY THE
PARK BUT TELL PEOPLE THIS PLACE
MATTERS.
>> THESE PLACES ARE SET ASIDE TO
BE BECAUSE THEY'RE SPECIAL.
THESE PLACES ARE CHANGING, AND
CHANGING FAST.
>> IT'S GORGEOUS.
AND WE ARE WORRIED ABOUT THE
RECEDING
GLACIERS.
>> WHILE TEMPERATURES ARE ON THE
RISE ACROSS MONTANA, MONTANA IS
WARMING TWICE AS FAST.
TAKE ACCORDING TO THE
GOVERNMENT'S OWN CLIMATE
ASSESSMENT.
THE STATE IS HOME TO TINY COOL
TOWNS WHICH HAVE HISTORICALLY
PROVIDED THE COUNTRY WITH NEEDS,
AN AREA WITH TREASURED NATURAL
WONDERS.
ANY TIME YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT
CLIMATE AND POLITICS IN AMERICA,
GLACIER NATIONAL PARK HAS TO BE
PART OF THE CONVERSATION.
THERE ARE AN ESTIMATED 150
GLACIERS HERE IN 1850.
TODAY THERE'S ONLY 25.
FEWER DAYS BELOW FREEZING AND
MORE ABOVE 90 DEGREES IS
CHANGING THE STATE.
LESS SNOWFALL AND EARLIER MELT
EACH YEAR MEANS MORE FIRES.
THEY'RE BIGGER AND BURNING
LONGER.
PROFESSOR DIANA SIKS.
>> WE ARE JUST SEEING A LOT OF
FIRES NOW.
>> DAN FAYE MEASURES THE
DISAPPEARING GLACIERS FOR THE
U.S. GEOLOGICAL SURVEY.
HIS FIELD OF CHANGE IS WIDENING.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE CHANGES LIKE
THIS THEY TEND TO CASCADE
THROUGH THE SYSTEM.
THE SAME THINGS MELTING THE
GLACIERS ARE CAUSING CHANGES IN
FOREST FIRE FREQUENCY AND
SEVERITY.
>> THE CURRENT ADMINISTRATION
SAYS THEY DON'T LOSE SLEEP ABOUT
THIS, I CERTAINLY DO.
>> MONTANA GOVERNOR STEVE
BULLOCK IS TRYING TO FIND A WAY
TO BALANCE THE REALITIES OF
CLIMATE CHANGE IN A STATE WITH
AN ENERGY INDUSTRY THAT DEPENDS
ON COAL, ALL THE WHILE DOING IT
WHILE RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT
INSIDE THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
>> AS WE MAKE TRANSITIONS, WE
CAN'T BE LEAVING COMMUNITIES
BEHIND.
THERE ARE FOLKS THAT, YOU KNOW,
THEY'VE WORKED THEIR WHOLE LIFE
POWERING THIS COUNTRY, AND AT
TIMES -- AND DEMOCRATS AND
OTHERS -- TRY TO MAKE THEM INTO
THE VILLAINS.
>> FOR SMALL TOWNS LIKE COOL
STRIP, MONTANA, ANY DISCUSSION
OF CLIMATE CHANGE WILL BE A
DISCUSSION ABOUT REVENUE AND
JOBS.
THE PLANT BEHIND ME IS WITHIN
CITY LIMITS.
BETWEEN THAT AND A COAL MINE,
OFFICIALS HERE SAY IT ACCOUNTS
FOR 90% OF THE TOWN'S REVENUE.
TWO BUILDINGS AT COOL STRIP
POWER PLANT IN OPERATION SINCE
THE MID '70s WILL SHUT DOWN JUST
A WEEK AFTER CHRISTMAS.
>> YOU ARE GOING TO SEE A DROP
IN REVENUE LOCALLY.
>> Reporter: LAURA SHAW IS A
FORMER CITY COUNCIL MEMBER.
SHE'S ALSO THE FOUNDER OF COOL
STRIP UNITED, A PRO-COOL
ADVOCACY GROUP.
>> WHEN A TOWN, A STATE, A
COMMUNITY IS WHOLLY RELIANT ON
ONLY ONE OR TWO INDUSTRIES, THAT
MAKES US VULNERABLE.
I THINK WE SHOULD BE ALWAYS
LOOKING FOR WAYS TO DIVERSIFY
AND BECOME MORE RESILIENT.
>> Reporter: EVEN WHILE FACED
WITH CERTAIN ECONOMIC COLLAPSE,
MANY HERE WANT PEOPLE OUTSIDE
MONTANA TO KNOW THEY UNDERSTAND
THE DIFFICULT BALANCE.
>> WE'RE NOT JUST LIKE A BUNCH
OF NATURE-HATING MONSTERS, YOU
KNOW.
WE HAVE OUR LIVES HERE AND WE
HAVE FAMILIES.
>> I BELIEVE THAT WE NEED TO
HAVE A BEAUTIFUL ENVIRONMENT,
BUT WHAT PEOPLE DON'T GET IS
COAL GOT US WHERE WE ARE.
>> CLIMATE CHANGE IS REAL.
WE MIGHT BE NOT LEAVING ANYTHING
FOR OUR CHILDREN OR
GRANDCHILDREN IF WE'RE NOT
CAREFUL, SO WE HAVE TO ADDRESS
IT.
>> WE HAVE TO ADDRESS CLIMATE
CHANGE AND WE HAVE TO DO IT NOW,
AND WE ACTUALLY ARE AT THE POINT
NOW IN A COUNTRY WHERE MAYBE IT
WAS LIP SERVICE 30 YEARS AGO,
BUT IF WE'RE NOT TAKING
IMMEDIATE AND DURABLE ACTION NOW
THE AMERICA WE'RE GOING TO GIVE
AND THE WORLD THAT WE'RE GOING
TO GIVE TO OUR KIDS AND GRAND
KIDS ISN'T GOING TO BE THE
AMERICA WE LIVE IN.
>> CASEY, THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION NOT ONLY DOESN'T
WANT TO HAVE THIS CONVERSATION,
THEY'RE ACTIVELY TRYING TO
PREVENT PEOPLE FROM HAVING THE
CONVERSATION, INCLUDING PEOPLE
THAT WORK FOR THE U.S.
GOVERNMENT.
FOR THE DEMOCRATS' PART, THE DNC
SAID THEY'RE NOT HAVING A
STAND-ALONE DEBATE ON CLIMATE
CHANGE.
HOWEVER, AS RACHEL MADDOW WOULD
SAY, WATCH THIS SPACE BECAUSE WE
UNDERSTAND THEY'RE REDISCUSSING
THAT AND THERE COULD BE A VOTE
IN AUGUST.
SO WE MAY HAVE A CLIMATE CHANGE
FORUM ON THE HORIZON, CASEY.
>> IT WILL BE INTERESTING TO SEE
IF THEY DECIDE IT IS SOMETHING
THAT DESERVES -- THEY RECEIVED A
LOT OF CRITICISM FOR SAYING,
HEY, WE CAN'T SPEND AN ENTIRE
EVENING TALKING ABOUT THIS WHEN,
OF COURSE, IT IS SOMETHING
THAT'S GOING TO DRAMATICALLY
AFFECT ALL OF US.
CAL PERRY, THANK YOU FOR YOUR
REPORTING.
IT LOOKED LIKE A FANTASTIC,
BEAUTIFUL TRIP TO MONTANA.
COMING UP NEXT, A TENNIS PRODIGY
TAKES DOWN A TENNIS TITAN WHO
HAPPENS TO BE HER IDOL.
ONE MORE THING, NEXT.
OL
ONE MORE THING, NEXT
>>> ONE MORE THING BEFORE WE GO.
MEET COREY COCO GAUFF.
SHE'S 15 YEARS OLD.
BORN IN ATLANTA, SHE STARTED
PLAYING TENNIS AT THE AGE OF 7,
INSPIRED BY WHO ELSE?
VENUS AND SERENA WILLIAMS.
AFTER NOTICING SHE HAD A KNACK
FOR IT ON THE COURT, HER FAMILY
MOVED TO FLORIDA TO GIVE HER
BETTER OPPORTUNITIES TO TRAIN.
BY THE TIME CORI WAS 11, SHE HAD
THE CHANCE TO TRAIN WITH SERENA
WILLIAMS AS COACH IN FRANCE, AND
BY 14 SHE HAD WON HER FIRST
MATCH AS A PROFESSIONAL.
JUST A FEW MONTHS LATER SHE WAS
SIGNED BY NEW BALANCE.
DESPITE ACHIEVING SO MUCH IN HER
SHORT 15 YEARS, NOTHING COULD
HAVE PREPARED HER FOR WHAT WAS
TO COME.
FIRST CAME FRIDAY WHEN COCO
BECAME THE YOUNGEST PERSON TO
QUALIFY FOR THE MAIN DRAW AT
WIMBLEDON.
SHE SAID RIGHT AFTERWARD THAT
SHE HOPED THAT MAYBE SHE COULD
PLAY AGAINST ONE OF HER IDOLS.
SO THEN CAME YESTERDAY.
SHE TOOK THE COURT AT WIMBLEDON,
AND ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE NET
SEVEN-TIME GRAND SLAM CHAMPION
VENUS WILLIAMS, COCO'S DREAM
COME TRUE, TAKING ON ONE OF THE
VERY WOMEN WHO INSPIRED HER TO
PICK UP A RACKET IN THE FIRST
PLACE.
THERE THEY WERE, THE YOUNGEST AT
WIMBLEDON, COCO, VERSUS THE
ELDEST AT WIMBLEDON, VENUS
WILLIAMS, 39 YEARS OLD.
NO ONE, AND I MEAN NO ONE COULD
HAVE PREDICTED WHAT THIS 15-YEAR
OLD WOULD DO NEXT.
>> STANDING OVATION!
COCO GAUFF CONQUERS VENUS
WILLIAMS.
>> JUST UNBELIEVABLE.
COCO BECOMING THE YOUNGEST
PLAYER SINCE 1991 TO WIN IN THE
FIRST ROUND OF THE WOMEN'S
TOURNAMENT.
A RISING STAR TAKING DOWN A
TITAN IN STRAIGHT SETS, COCO
OVERCOME WITH EMOTION, AS YOU
WOULD EXPECT.
HER PARENTS BEAMING WITH PRIDE
FROM THE STANDS.
SO WHAT DOES A TEEN STAR TELL
HER IDOL AFTER BESTING HER IN
FRONT OF THE WHOLE WORLD?
>> AFTER THE MATCH I TOLD HER
THAT JUST THANK YOU FOR
EVERYTHING SHE DID.
I WOULDN'T BE HERE IF IT WASN'T