HURT ME.
>> LeBRON WAS JULY 9th, JULY
10th.
KEVIN DURANT WAS JULY 4th.
>> IT'S NOT UNUSUAL.
WE'VE SEEN SUCH AN ACCELERATION
IN THE WAY FREE AGENCY WORKS.
WE'VE NEVER SEEN THIS MUCH
MONEY.
>> NO.
IT'S OVER $4 MILLION.
>> WE'RE ON DAY FOUR.
CALM DOWN.
BE ZEN.
WE'LL GET YOU THROUGH THE KAWHI
LIGHT ZONE.
WE'RE BACK TONIGHT AT 7:00
EASTERN.
COME RIGHT BACK.
WE'LL BE HERE WAITING FOR YOU.
DOUG: STRAIGHT AHEAD ON
"DAILY WAGER", THE DOG
DAYS OF SUMMER ARE
HERE.
HOW A HOLIDAY HEAT WAVE
COULD AFFECT BASEBALL
TOTALS ACROSS THE NEXT
FEW DAYS, AND COULD
THAT SUNSHINE ALSO
AFFECT HOT DOGS
CAPTIONING MADE
POSSIBLE BY ESPN, INC.
DOUG: WE HOPE TO MAKE
YOU A MORE INFORMED
SPORTS BETTER.
WE HAVE A PACKED SHOW
COMING UP.
WHO KNOWS, KAWHI COULD
MAYBE MAKE A DECISION
AT ANY SECOND E, AND
THAT WOULD TURN THE NBA
FUTURE ODDS UPSIDE
DOWN.
UNTIL THEN, LET'S GET
ROLLING WITH THE REST
OF THE SHOW, WHICH
INCLUDES THE SUBWAY
SERIES.
FIRST PITCH, ABOUT AN
HOUR AWAY.
METS BEAT THE YANKS
LAST NIGHT.
HE HAD AN E.R.A. IN
8 1/2 BEFORE A HIP
INJURY.
JASON VARGAS, HE IS
2.36 E.R.A. IN THE LAST
SEVEN STARTS.
THE BOMBERS ARE FAVORED
FOR THE GAME AND THE
FIRST FIVE AND THE RUN
TOTAL IS TEN.
TEN.
JOE JOINS ME FROM THE
BAY AREA HERE.
JOE, WHAT'S YOUR PLAY
IN THIS ONE.
JOE: IT MAY SOUND
CRAZY, BUT I LIKE THE
METS AT PLUS 130 IN
THIS MATCHUP.
THE YANKS SCORED JUST
TWO RUNS IN THAT GAME
LAST NIGHT AGAINST THE
METS.
THAT WAS JUST THE THIRD
TIME IN THEIR LAST 39
GAMES THAT THEY SCORED
TWO OR FEWER RUNS.
NOW, A LOT OF THAT IS
DUE CREDIT TO ZACH
WHEELER AND THE METS
BULLPEN WHICH SHOWED UP
LAST NIGHT, BUT I GOT
TO WONDER AFTER THAT
SERIES ACROSS THE POND
AGAINST THE RED SOX,
MAYBE THERE'S A LITTLE
JET LAG AND FATIGUE AT
PLAY HERE FOR THE
YANKEES.
DUG I'VE HEARD THE
WHOLE JET LAG THING,
BUT THE BOSTON RED SOX
DID PUT UP TEN RUNS OR
MAYBE THE BLUE JAYS
WERE JUST THAT BAD
YESTERDAY.
WE SHOULD SEE.
YOU'RE ON THE METS.
I KNOW I TALKED TO YOU
YESTERDAY.
MY APOLOGIES.
YANKS-METS.
ONE OF JUST -- JUST ONE
OF FIVE GAMES TONIGHT
WITH A TOTAL OF AT
LEAST TEN RUNS.
ASTROS-ROCKIES LEADING
THE WAY WITH A TOTAL OF
14 1/2.
DOUG: WHAT DO YOU HAVE
IN TERMS OF OVER-UNDER?
>> IT'S AT
ASTROS-ROCKIES UNDER
14 1/2.
MY PROJECTION IS 13.1
RUNS, AND THAT ACCOUNTS
FOR 9-MILE-AN-HOUR
WINDS, AND IT ACTS FOR
THE FACT THAT THEY'RE
PLAYING AT COORS FIELD.
WE EVEN TALKED ABOUT
YESTERDAY, IT'S CRAZY
HAVING THESE ASTROS
BATS.
THEY'RE SO MUCH BETTER
THAN THE ROCKIES
HITTING IN COORS FIELD,
AND I STILL LOOKING AT
THIS -- THIS GUY HAS
BEEN JUST STELLAR FOR
TWO YEARS, AND IF YOU
SAY, OH, COME ON FROM
THE AMERICAN LEAGUE,
PITCHING IN COORS FOR
THE FIRST TIME, HE WAS
WITH THE DIAMONDBACKS.
HE WAS ACCUSTOMED TO
PITCHING IN COORS.
EXPECTED BATTING
AVERAGE AGAINST ALL OF
THESE METRICS, AND ON
THE OTHER SIDE LAMBERT,
HE IS THE NUMBER ONE
PROSPECT FOR THE
ROCKIES.
THAT IS THE CONCERN
SOME IS THAT THE ASTROS
JUST GO NUTS.
I HAVE IT RIGHT AT 13
ALMOST.
I GOT TO GO UNDER.
DOUG: ON THOSE LIST OF
DOUBLE DIGIT TOTALS I
WOULD GO OVER 11 1/2
WITH THE PHILLIES AND
BRAVES.
BOTH PITCHERS HAVE
REALLY STRUGGLED.
BRYCE WILSON E.R.A.
OVER EIGHT AND -- I'M
NOT GOING TO OVER THINK
IT.
I'LL TAKE THE OVER IN
THAT ONE.
PRESTON, SIT TIGHT FOR
THAT, AND JOE, WHAT
ABOUT YOU ON THAT LIST
OF OVER-UNDER AND
DOUBLE DIGITS?
WHICH ONE JUMPED OUT TO
YOU?
PERHAPS THE SECOND HALF
OF THE DOUBLE-HEADER.
THEY'RE TIRED.
THEY'VE BEEN OUT ON THE
DIAMOND ALL DAY.
THIS KID WILL BE ABLE
TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF
THEM A LITTLE BIT, AND
NOT ONLY THAT, CHICAGO
IS ABOUT MIDDLE OF THE
PACK IN OPS AGAINST
LEFT-HANDED PITCHING.
NOW, ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE EQUATION, SAYS
IT'S GOING TO BE ROSS
DETWIELER WHO EARNED
HIS MAJOR LEAGUE
VICTORY IN THREE YEARS
HIS FIRST TIME OUT A
WEEK AGO.
WENT UP AGAINST
MINNESOTA.
LOOKED REALLY SHARP.
GAVE UP JUST TWO EARNED
RUNS IN FIVE INNINGS
PITCHED.
HE WILL GO UP AGAINST
THE TIGER LINE-UP
TONIGHT.
THAT'S 25th IN OPS
AGAINST LEFT-HANDED
PITCHING.
I THINK THE PITCHERS
HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF
SUCCESS.
WE PLAY THE UNDER
10 1/2 RUNS.
WHITE SOX-TIGERS.
DOUG: SOUNDS GOOD.
SIT TIGHT.
MUCH MORE FROM YOU AND
PRESTON THROUGHOUT THE
SHOW, AND WE TALKED
COLLEGE FOOTBALL IN
RECENT SHOWS.
BIG TEN YESTERDAY.
I ALSO COVERED THE
S.E.C.
A LITTLE ACC.
HERE'S A LOOK AT YOUR
HIGHEST -- SIXTH
HIGHEST WIN TOTALS
COURTESY OF CEASAR'S
FOR THE COMING SEASON.
NO SURPRISE.
CLEMSON WITH A SIZABLE
GAP OVER THE REST OF
THE CONFERENCE.
11 1/2, MINUS 110
EITHER SIDE.
OBVIOUSLY, TREVOR
LAWRENCE RETURNS FOR
THE DEFEND DEFENDING
NATIONAL CHAMPIONS.
MIAMI AT 8 1/2.
VIRGINIA EASTBOUNDING
IT AT 8 AND A TRIO OF
NC STATE, SYRACUSE, AND
VIRGINIA ALL AT 7 1/2.
JUICES ON THAT.
LET'S WELCOME IN THE
BEAR, CHRIS FELICA AND
STANFORD STEVE.
I KNEW YOU GUYS WERE
CLOSE.
THE BEAR: ABSOLUTELY.
LET'S GO.
DOUG: I'M GOING TO
START WITH THE
DEFENDING CHAMPS.
CLEMSON 11 1/2.
>> UNDER.
DOUG: OVER.
LOOK, THIS IS SCI, OUR
FOOTBALL POWER INDEX
PROJECTS THEM TO WIN
ALL THEIR GAMES BY AT
LEAST 20, EXCEPT FOR
TWO.
HOME TO A&M AND THAT'S
15, AND THEN AT SOUTH
CAROLINA 18.
ALL OF THEM BY AT LEAST
TWO TOUCHDOWNS.
THEY'RE ONLY KIND OF
QUESTIONABLE GAMES ARE
AT HOME OR JUST NOT
THAT -- IT SHOULD BE
WIRE TO WIRE.
I THINK ALABAMA BEING
IN THE RACE YOU'RE
GOING TO HEAR A LOT
ABOUT THAT.
WE'LL KEEP THEM ON
POINTED.
WE TEND TO THINK, OH,
CLEMSON ALWAYS WILL
DROP ONE.
THEY DIDN'T LAST YEAR.
WE CAN'T ASSUME THAT,
AND I THINK OVER
11 1/2.
>> THE WHOLE CLEMSON
THING, THAT'S LONG
GONE.
THE ONLY THING THAT
I -- I WOULD PLAY THE
OVER ON THAT AS WELL.
THE ONLY THING I
WOULD -- THAT COULD
TRIP THEM UP IS THE
INJURY WHICH NOBODY
WANTS TO SEE, BUT --
DOUG: THEY'RE A&M AT
HOME.
THE SCHEDULE IS
FAVORABLE FOR THEM TO
RUN THE TABLE.
>> I THINK THE
CONFERENCE IS TERRIBLE.
DOUG: BRUTAL.
FIRE AWAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'LL START.
ON THE OTHER SIDE, I
LOOK AT FLORIDA STATE,
OKAY?
NOW, THEY WERE AT A
DISASTER LAST YEAR,
OKAY?
THEY WON FIVE GAMES.
THEY STARTED NINE
DIFFERENT COMBINATIONS
ON THE OFFENSIVE LINE.
OKAY?
YOU KNOW, QUARTERBACKS
WERE COMING IN AND OUT
OF THERE.
DEFENSIVELY THEY WERE
AWFUL.
THEY DIDN'T RANK IN THE
TOP 1 00 IN ANY
DEFENSIVE CATEGORIES.
THE BEAR: THEY WERE ON
SHORT FIELD.
>> I THINK THEY AVERAGE
THE 265 YARDS A GAME.
21 POINT
>> GUYS ARE HAVING TO
PLAY.
DUG WHO, THE KOECHSZ?
A LOT OF REASONS.
WITH THE COMBINATIONS
OF ROSTER, OKAY, AND
THEN THE SCHEDULE,
OKAY, I THINK IT'S
DOABLE.
THE NUMBER 7.
THEY HAVE THE TALENT TO
DO IT.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE
SCHEDULE, FIVE OF THE
TEAMS, ALL RIGHT, WON
NINE GAMES LAST YEAR.
THAT'S A BIG DROP-OFF.
THOSE TEAMS LOST A LOT
OF GAMES.
AND I THINK IT'S PRETTY
FAVORABLE WHEN YOU LOOK
AT EVERYTHING.
I TAKE THREE GAMES THAT
AREN'T WINNABLE AT
CLEMSON, AT FLORIDA, AT
VIRGINIA.
THE BEAR: WE TALKED
LAST WEEK ABOUT THOSE
LINES WHEN AT THE CAME
OUT.
I LIKE FLORIDA STATE IN
THAT GAME.
YOU CANNOT GO TO
VIRGINIA WITH THE
CHANCE THAT THEY COULD
BE 1-2 OFF THE BAT OFF
THE YEAR THAT YOU HAD
LAST YEAR.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU THINK KENDALL, THE
BIGGEST COORDINATOR
HIRE.
MAYBE EVEN HIM OR AL
FINCH.
DOUG: YEAH.
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO
PLAY WITH?
BLACKMAN, TWO YEARS
AGO.
DOUG: IS THE NUMBER ONE
RECRUIT.
HE HAS DEMONSTRATED
THAT IN FLORIDA, AND HE
HAS ANOTHER YEAR TO
IMPLEMENT ALL THOSE
GUYS.
NOT WHO IS GOING TO
PLAY SKREM E CLEMSON
AND -- WHO IS THE
SECOND BEST TEAM?
WHEN YOU LOOK AT IT,
YOU KNOW, THREE MONTHS
AGO YOU ASKED A
QUESTION WHEN WE DID
LIKE THE KENTUCKY
DERBY.
SYRACUSE, THEY LOOKED
GREAT.
DOUG: FPI SAYS 8.1 WIN.
>> ALL THOSE GUYS ARE
DEFENSE.
GONE.
I'M ON THE UNDER THIS
YEA
>> I DON'T KNOW IF YOU
CAN LINE UP THAT
OFFENSIVE LINE AND DEAL
35 TIMES LIKE THEY
WANT.
THEY HAVE A COORDINATOR
CHANGE ON BOTH SIDES OF
THE BALL.
WE'LL SEE HOW THAT
GOES.
THEY'VE BEEN A SIX OR
SEVEN WIN TEAM EVERY
YEAR UNDER HIM.
YOU LOOK AT VIRGINIA
TECH TO START THE
OPENING UP.
THEY SHOULD WIN THE
NEXT THREE.
I'M HIGH ON WAKE
FOREST.
I THINK THEY'RE GOING
TO BE REALLY GOOD.
LOOK AT THE WAY THEY
FINISH.
THOSE FINAL FIVE GAMES,
IF THEY HAVEN'T GOTTEN
TO SEVEN BY THE TIME
THEY GO TO CLEMSON,
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO.
STEVE: THAT'S WHY I
LIKE FLORIDA STATE OVER
AND --
>> THEY JUST RELOAD.
SOMETHING LIKE BC --
THEY DEVELOP PRAYERS
AND FIND GUYS THAT THEY
GET INTO THEIR SYSTEM,
AND I THINK IT'S A
YOUNG OFFENSIVE LINE.
I'M THINKING THEY'RE.
DOUG: 5.1.
STEVE: DO YOU HAVE A
CALCULATOR OVER THERE?
DOUG: SPREADSHEET.
MY COMPUTER MODEL.
THE BEAR: PROBABLY DID
TAKE IT.
STEVE: VIRGINIA AND I
HAVE A THING.
THEY LOOK GOOD.
THE BEAR: THEY DO?
DUG WE HAVE PRESENT OF
TIME.
WE HAVE GAME ONE --
WEEK ONE LINES WE CAN
DISSECT AS WELL
THROUGHOUT THE REST OF
THE SUMMER.
BEAR AND STANFORD STEVE
HERE IN THE HOUSE.
WE ALL LIKE A LITTLE
TENNIS ACTION.
ESPECIALLY IN THE
MORNING, RIGHT?
FIRE AWAY ON BRAD
GILBERT AND WIMBLEDON
UNDERDOG GALORE.
WE'LL HAVE PATRICK
McENROE NEXT WITH
PICKS.
WHERE DO YOU STAND ON
ANDREW LUCK PASSING
TOUCHDOWNS THIS YEAR?
32 1/2.
WE'LL BREAK IT DOWN AS
"DAILY WAGER" ROLLS ON.
What makes DiGiorno Crispy Pan
Pizza different than delivery?
♪ PAN PAN PAN PAAAAN ♪
You bake it fresh
in its own pan!
Giving our DiGiorno pizza
a crispy, caramelized crust.
♪ PAAAAN ♪
It's not Delivery,
It's DiGiorno.
(VO)
Why use Post-it Extreme Notes?
Because they make your message
stick,
getting it said, and done right,
the first time.
(Man off screen)
Aw, C'mon!
(VO)
Stop the Re-work with Post-it
Extreme Notes.
♪ I'm tasting olives... ♪
♪ Roasted pine nuts... ♪
♪ Mmm this red pepper... ♪
♪ That's spicy stuff... ♪
Fresh flavor. Feel good food.
Sabra Hummus.
♪ I just had Sabra Hummus and
now I feel good! ♪
So I can buy from
Enterprise Car Sales and you'll
take ANY trade-in?
That's right!
Great!
Here you go...
Well, it does need
to be a vehicle.
But - I need this out of
my house.
(VO) With fair, transparent
value for every trade-in...
Enterprise makes it easy.
Hiyeeeeeee!
Oh!
We all just got new
smartphones at Cricket!
Hiyeeeeeee!
!Holaaaaa!
OK, biyeeeeee!
Biyeeeee!!
[ dogs barking ]
OK, biyeeeeee!
What about him?
Let's do it.
[ sniffing ]
Come on.
This summer, add a new
member to the family.
Hurry into the Mercedes-Benz
Summer Event today
for exceptional offers.
Lease the GLC 300 SUV
for just $419 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz Summer
Event. Going on now.
DUG BACK WITH YOU ON
"DAILY WAGER".
WIMBLEDON JUST
RECAPPING SOME OF THE
ACTION.
THE BIGGEST STORY
PROBABLY IS COCO GAUF,
THE 15-YEAR-OLD
AMERICAN.
WHAT A STORY.
SHE WON TODAY AS A PLUS
155 UNDERDOG.
SHE MOVES ON FOR THE
THIRD ROUND TO HERTZOG.
WE WENT OUT YESTERDAY
AS A WINNER.
WHAT ELSE IS GOING ON?
LOTS OF UPSETS SO FAR.
BOTH PLAYERS HAVE SPLIT
SIX CAREER MEETINGS.
ON THE WOMEN'S SIDE 11
SEED SERENA WILLIAMS IS
GOING TO FACE A
QUALIFIER.
SHE'S A PERFECT 18-0 IN
SECOND ROUND MATCHES IN
THE ALL ENGLAND CLUB,
AND IS A MINUS 750
FAVORITE.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT
SOME OF THE OTHER
NOTABLE MATCHUPS AS WE
CATCH OUR EYE.
ANG LEAK MINUS 950.
HEY, YOU DON'T LIKE THE
BIG JUICE.
YOU DON'T WANT TO LAY
THE LUMBER.
YOU CAN ALWAYS DO A
MONEY LINE PARLAY AND
SAM QUERY WITH THE
UPSET IS MINUS 460 IN
HIS SECOND MATCH.
AS FOR A COUPLE OF
POTENTIAL UPSETS AND
OTHER PICKS, LET'S TURN
IT OVER TO OUR PATRICK
McENROE.
>> EXPECTING MORE
BEAUTIFUL WEATHER, AND
THE MATCH WE'VE ALL
BEEN WAITING FOR ON THE
MEN'S SIDE IN ROUND TWO
THAT WILL BE BETWEEN
THE TWO-TIME CHAMP
RAFAEL NADAL AND THE
WHACKY ONE FROM
AUSTRALIA NICK WHO CAN
ALSO PLAY SERIOUS
TENNIS, PARTICULARLY ON
GRASS.
REMEMBER, A COUPLE OF
YEARS AGO HE UPSET
NADAL RIGHT HERE AT
WIMBLEDON ON CENTER
COURT.
I'M NOT EXPECTING THAT
TO HAPPEN TOMORROW.
I THINK NADAL IS READY
FOR THIS ACCIDENT,
HAVING WON THE FRENCH
OPEN.
HE HAS SOME CONFIDENCE.
THIS IS HIS LEAST
FAVORITE SURFACE.
THE FAVORITE.
HE HAS NOT LOOKED LIKE
THE PLAYER HE WAS A
COUPLE OF YEARS AGO.
I EXPECT NADAL TO MAYBE
DROP A SET, BUT
PROBABLY WIN THIS ONE
IN FOUR SETS.
I EXPECT HER TO WIN
COMFORTABLY IN STRAIGHT
SETS.
BACK TO YOU, DOUG.
DOUG: PATRICK, THANKS
SO MUCH.
LOOK, IT'S INDEPENDENCE
DAY, AND FIRE AWAY IN
THE MORNING, THROUGHOUT
THE AFTERNOON.
YOU GOT SOME BASEBALL
ON JULY 4th.
HE IS STREAMING LIVE ON
THE ESPN APP.
WE'VE BEEN TALKING A
LOT OF PRO FOOTBALL
PROPS.
TOURS OF EACH DIVISION.
WE'RE DOING THE SOUTH
DIVISIONS THIS WEEK.
AC SOUTH WITH THE COLT.
PLAYER PROP COURTESY OF
CEASAR'S.
ANDREW LUCK TOUCHDOWN
TOTAL 32 1/2.
HE HAS GONE OVER JUST
TWICE IN HIS FIVE FULL
SEASONS.
MARLIN NEEDS A 1,000
YARD RUSHING SEASON TO
GO OVER HIS STOELGTS.
THE COLTS HAVE HAD ONE
1 ,000 YARD RUSHER IN
THE LAST DECADE.
THAT WAS FRANK GORE IN
2016.
LET'S BRING IN NOW OUR
MALE MODELERS, PRESTON
JOHNSON AND MIKE CLAY
WHO HAVE SPREADSHEETS
AND LAPTOPS IN HAND AS
WE BREAK THIS DOWN.
ANDREW LUCK, 32TD
PASSES.
WHAT ARE YOUR NUMBERS
SAYING, MIKE?
MIKE: GOING OVER ON
THIS ONE.
THIS GUY IS 39 PASSING
TOUCHDOWNS LAST SEASON.
THAT WAS SECOND MOST IN
THE NFL BEHIND ONLY --
YOU MAY HAVE HEARD OF
HIM.
THE LAST TIME WE SAW
ANDREW LUCK FOR A FULL
16 GAME SEASON, HE HAD
40 PASSING TOUCHDOWNS,
AND REALLY THE KEY HERE
IS OPPORTUNITY.
YOU HAVE AN OTD WHICH
WAS SET ESSENTIALLY
EXPECTED -- EXPECTED
PASSING TOUCHDOWNS
BASED ON YOUR
OPPORTUNITY WHERE YOU
ARE ON THE FIELD AND
YOUR VOLUME OF THROWS.
LUCK LAST YEAR, TOPS IN
THE NFL.
34.0.
THE KEY THROWN INTO THE
END ZONE.
THE COLTS HAD 50 LAST
SEASON.
THAT WAS MOST IN THE
LEAGUE.
THIS OFFENSE STEPPED UP
FOR HIM TO THROW A TON
OF TOUCHDOWNS.
>> SOUNDS GOOD.
PRESTON, WHAT ARE YOUR
PROJECTIONS?
>> WE DO THIS EVERY
DAY, AND I HAD ANDREW
LUCK AT 28 TOUCHDOWNS,
AND I COULDN'T BELIEVE
IT.
THERE'S NO WAY I'M
BETTING UNDER ON THIS.
IF YOU LOOK AT IT, AND
I AGREE WITH MIKE,
LIKE, THERE'S SO MUCH
VALUE HERE WITH ANDREW
LUCK, ASSUMING HE PLAYS
A FULL SEASON.
I'M NOT SURE HOW HE
DOESN'T GO OVER 32 1/2.
I ACTUALLY AM STAYING
OFF OF THIS DESPITE MY
PROJECTIONS POINTING TO
AN EDGE ON THE UNDER,
BUT BECAUSE I AM LOWER
ON ANDREW LUCK'S
PROJECTIONS, THERE ARE
SOME CORRELATED BETS,
WHICH WE'LL GET TO HERE
IN A BIT, WHICH I THINK
ARE SAFER AND BETTER AS
FAR AS SOME OF THE
RECEIVERS GO?
>> BEING LOOK BACK AT
THE LAST THREE SEASONS
AND HOW THEY'VE PLAYED
TOGETHER IN FULL.
THEY'VE BLOWN THIS
NUMBER AWAY ALL THREE
SEASONS.
THERE'S A FEW THINGS IN
PLAY HERE.
ONE OF THE THEM IS
DURABILITY.
HE HAS MISSED FOUR
GAMES IN SEVEN SEASONS
IN THE LEAGUE.
HE FINISHED TOP 17 IN
RECEIVING YARDS.
EACH OF THE PAST SIX
SEASONS.
GUYS, HE HAS BEEN IN
THE 80th PERCENT I'LL
OR BETTER IN YARDS PER
RECEPTION EACH OF THE
PAST FIVE SEASONS.
IT'S ANDREW LUCK GOING
THROUGH GUYS.
THIS IS A HIGH VOLUME
PASS-HEAVY OFFENSE, AND
I THINK HE GETS TO THAT
NUMBER EASILY.
DOUG: PRESTON, AND YOU?
PRESTON: THIS ONE WHERE
WE DISAGREE.
I'M CORRELATED HERE
WITH NOT LOVING ANDREW
LUCK'S NUMBERS, BUT
HILTON I ATHE 1,140
YARDS.
FOR ME THERE IS A
SLIGHT EDGE TO THE
UNDER, AND YOU LOOK AT
THE SCOPE OF WHO LUCK
WILL BE THROWING TO.
THEY WENT OUT OF THEIR
WAY TO BRING IN DEVIN
AND DRAFTED PARIS
CAMPBELL OUT OF OHIO
STATE WHO I THINK WILL
BE STELLAR.
THEN HE PLAYED A BUNCH
LAST YEAR AT TIGHT END.
DOYLE POLICED A LOT OF
LAST SEASON.
I HAVE THOSE TWO
TIGHTENDS COMBINED.
I THINK TY HILTON IS
TARGET SHARE GOING
DOWN.
I HAVE HIM UNDER 1,200
YARDS.
IT'S A BET UNDER FOR
ME.
DOUG: I LIKE WHEN YOU
DISAGREE.
MIKE, LET'S GO TO YOU.
MARLIN MACK, WILL HE BE
A 1,000 YARD RUSHER.
NOT COMBINED.
JUST RUSHING YARDS.
>> YES, HE WILL.
HE SORT OF WAS LAST
YEAR.
YOU LOOK AT HIS 14
GAMES, INCLUDING THE
PLAYOFFS.
HE HAD A LITTLE OVER
1,100 YARDS, AND THAT
WAS WITH PLAYING A
SITUATIONAL ROLE FOR A
LOT OF THE EARLY PART
OF THE SEASON.
THE GUY HAS BEEN
TERRIFIC SINCE HE HAS
ENTERED THE LEAGUE, AND
HE HAD 4.8 YARDS PER
CARRY LAST SEASON.
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET
TOO WRAPPED UP IN YARDS
PER CARRY, BUT HE HAS
BEEN ABOVE AVERAGE
AFTER CONTACT PER
ATTEMPTS IN BOTH OF
THINKS NFL SEASONS.
HE HAD A LOT OF HELP
LAST SEASON FROM
QUINTON NELSON AS WELL.
HERE'S THE BIG ONE.
IN HIS LAST FIVE GAMES
LAST SEASON, HE HANDLED
AT LEAST 75% OF THE
COLTS DESIGNED RUNDZ
AND EACH OF THOSE
GAMES.
THE GUY IS WORKING HIS
WAY INTO BECOMING A
TWO-MAN WORK HORSE FOR
THIS COLTS OFFENSE.
I LIKE THE OVER A LOT
HERE.
DOUG: MIKE, YOU ARE
BULLISH ON THE COLTS'
OFFENSE.
YOU MENTIONED AIRCRAFT
HEBRON A MOMENT AGO.
SIX AND A HALF
TOUCHDOWNS FOR HIS
PROP.
WHERE ARE YOU HEADED
WITH THIS?
>> THIS IS ANOTHER GUT
CHECK.
I'M GOING WITH IT.
I HAVE PROJECTED 5.2
TOUCHDOWNS.
I MENTIONED JACK DOYLE
IS BACK.
HE SHOULD BE HEALTHIER,
AND I PROJECT HIM TO
HAVE A GOOD PORTION OF
THE SECOND TIGHT END OF
HIS POTENTIAL TARGET
SHARE.
DEVIN, THIS GUY IS
6'4", 240.
AS FAR AS RED ZONE
OPPORTUNITIES GO AND
GOAL LINE
OPPORTUNITIES, HEBRON
OUTSIDE OF LAST YEAR
WHERE HE SCORED 13
TOUCHDOWNS, THAT'S WHY
IT'S A GUT CHECK YOU
SHOULD SIX AND A HALF.
HE NEVER GOT MORE THAN
FIVE TOUCHDOWNS IN A
SEASON.
THAT WAS IN DETROIT.
MATTHEW STAFFORD IS NOT
INEPT.
THERE'S SO MUCH GOING
AROUND HERE FOR LUCK.
I HAVE TO GO UNDER.
DOUG: AGAIN, A LITTLE
TECHNICALITY AT TOTAL
TOUCHDOWNS.
A RECOVERED FUMBLE IN
THE GOAL LINE.
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> THAT CHANGES
EVERYTHING.
DOUG: YOU WANT TO GO
BACK TO YOUR
SPREADSHEET AND
RE-EVALUATE IT?
MORE TO COME FROM
PRESTON STRAIGHT AHEAD.
AND FROM PLAYER PROP TO
TEAM PROPS.
INDY'S WIN TOTAL IS
TEN, WHICH IS WHEN THEY
WON LAST YEAR.
THE OVER, PLUS 110, AND
THE YES-NO TO MAKE THE
PLAYOFFS.
YES IS MINUS $1.75,
WHICH THEY SURE, IN
FACT, DID IN FRANK
WRIGHT'S FIRST SEASON
WITH THE COLTS.
LET'S GO OUT TO NEW
YORK AND BRING IN OUR
ANITA MARKS.
ANITA, OVER-UNDER TEN.
NOW, I AM PASSING
BECAUSE I THINK IT'S
GOING TO BE RIGHT
THERE.
THEY HAVE TO FACE THE
NFC SOUTH.
REALLY TOUGH SCHEDULE.
SUPPOSED TO BE A
COMPETITIVE DIVISION.
IT'S GOING TO BE RIGHT
AROUND THERE.
I'M GOING TO PASS.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
ANITA: I'M ON THE OVER
A LITTLE BIT.
I'M NOT BANKING THE
MORTGAGE ON THE OVER,
BUT I AM PUTTING A
LITTLE MONEY ON THE
OVER FOR A NUMBER OF
REASONS.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
SCHEDULE.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT
THE SCHEDULE, ACTUALLY.
I HAVE THEM WINNING
THEIR DIVISION.
THE AFC SOUTH.
I THINK THEY SPLIT WITH
HOUSTON.
I THINK THEY GO 2-0
AGAINST TENNESSEE.
THEY COULD POSSIBLY GO
2-0 AGAINST THE
JAGUARS.
LOOKING AT 5-1, 4-3 IN
THEIR DIVISION.
EASY GAMES WITH ALL DUE
RESPECT TO OAKLAND,
DENVER, AND MIAMI.
HERE'S WHERE IT GETS
TOUGH.
LOOK AT THE ROAD GAMES
IN THE QUARTERBACKS
THEY'RE GOING TO BE
FACING.
YOU READY?
THE CHARGERS, THE
CHIEFS, THE STEELERS,
THE TEXANS, THE SAINTS.
IT'S A TOUGH ROAD GAME.
I HAVE THEM GOING 3-2
ON THE ROAD, SO IT'S
GOING TO BE CLOSE, BUT
I THINK THIS TEAM IS
JUST SO GOOD, DOUG,
THAT I HAVE THEM -- I
HAVE THEM AT 10-1 --
10, 11 WINS.
DOUG: I WAS DEFINITELY
LEANING THAT WAY, BUT
I'M GOING TO PASS.
AS FOR THE YES-NO, I
LIKE THE YES TO MAKE
THE PLAYOFFS AT MINUS
$1.75.
A LITTLE DIFFERENT THAN
THE DIVISION BECAUSE
YOU COULD GET TO THE
PLAYOFFS AND NOT GET
OVER TEN WINS.
NINE OR TEN WINS IN
THIS DIVISION COULD WIN
IT.
I'M GOING TO SAY I LIKE
THE YES TO MAKE THE
PLAYOFFS AT MINUS 1.75.
OBVIOUSLY, YOU HAVE THE
BONUS OF THE WILD CARD,
BUT THAT'S WHY I'M
DIFFERENTIATING BETWEEN
THAT AND OVER TEN WINS.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
ANITA: AGAIN, I HAVE
THEM WINNING THIS
DIVISION.
I LOVE THIS TEAM.
OUT OF ALL THE 22
STARTERS ON OFFENSE AND
DEFENSE, THEY ONLY HAVE
ONE GUY NOT COMING
BACK.
THAT'S AMAZING.
THAT JUST DOESN'T
HAPPEN IN THIS DAY AND
AGE IN FREE AGENCY.
ON TOP OF THAT, THEY
ARE ONE OF THE MOST
BALANCED TEAMS IN THE
NFL.
FIRST AND THIRD DOWN
CONVERSIONS IN 2018.
ANDREW LUCK, WHEN HE IS
HEALTHY, HE IS A TOP
FIVE QUARTERBACK.
HE HAS THE BEST
OFFENSIVE LINE COMING
IN.
WIDE RECEIVERS, YOU GOT
TO LOVE TY HILTON AND
ADD DEVIN FUNCHES.
THEY DRAFT PAIR
CAMPBELL.
I LOVE THE ONE-TWO
PUNCH WITH THEIR TIGHT
END.
EBRON TOOK A BIG STEP
WITH THEM THIS YEAR AS
OPPOSED WHAT WITH HE
SAW IN DETROIT.
JACK DOYLE, HE IS GOING
TO BE HEALTHY.
THEN THEY ADD JUSTIN
HOUSTON ON THE
DEFENSIVE SIDE OF THE
BALL, SO I JUST LOVE
THIS TEAM.
I THINK THEY'RE GOING
TO MAKE THE PLAYOFFS.
I THINK THEY WIN THE
DIVISION, DOUG.
DOUG: SOUNDS LIKE WE'RE
ALL VERY POSITIVE ON
THE COLTS.
THAT'S ANITA MARKS.
SHE'LL JOIN US LATER IN
THE SHOW TO DISCUSS THE
WEEKEND PGA TOURNAMENT.
THAT'S COMING UP LATER.
ANITA: THERE YOU GO.
DOUG: AND WE'RE
APPROACHING THE BOTTOM
OF THE HOUR, AND IN
THESE PARTS THAT MEANS
ONE THING.
BEST BETS.
JUST AROUND THE CORNER.
STAY TUNED.
♪  ♪
New for summer.
Here for summer.
Arriving...this summer.
It's Bud Light Lemon Tea.
New for summer.
♪How can I find a way without♪
♪Your Mexican Spice♪
You've heard the phenomenon.
Now experience Nacho fries
live from your house.
With Taco Bell delivery.
Tell him we're flexible.
Don't worry. My Dutch is OK.
Just OK?
(in Dutch)
Tell him we need this merger.
It's happening..!
Just OK is not OK.
Especially when it comes to
your network.
AT&T is America's best wireless
network
according to America's biggest
test.
Now with 5G Evolution.
The First Step to 5G.
More for your thing. That's our
thing.
DOUG: BACK WITITH YOU
RECAPPING BEBEST BETS.
STRONG NIGHT FOR US ON
THE DIAMOND.
ASTROS GOT FOUR RUNS IN
THE SEVENTH.
TURNED A THREE-RUN
DEFICIT INTO A ONE-RUN
VICTORY.
PLUS 117 FOR PRESTON
THERE ON THE STROS.
A'S HIT FOR JOE.
MY RAYS-DODGERS PARLAY
GOT THIS THANKS TO FIVE
CONSECUTIVE WALKS.
BETTER LUCKY THAN GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
SO 5-2 FROM THE WEEK.
LET'S KEEP THE MOMENTUM
GOING.
HERE AT THE DESK
STANFORD STEVE HERE
STANDING BY FOR YOUR
BEST BET.
WE'LL GET THAT IN A
MOMENT.
LET'S GO BACK OUT TO
LAS VEGAS.
PRESTON, WHAT DO YOU
HAVE FOR YOUR BEST BET?
YOU'RE ON THE TEE BOX
FIRST.
PRESTON: THE GRIZZLIES
MINUS 2 1/2.
THE ONLY GUY GETTING
RUNS THAT HAS ANY PRO
EXPERIENCE IS NAZ WHO
PLAYED A TOTAL OF 85
MINUTES FOR THE JAZZ
THE LAST TWO YEARS.
ON THE OTHER SIDE THIS
MEMPHIS TEAM, THIS IS A
ROSTER FILLED WITH A
BUNCH OF GUYS WHO
PLAYED FAIRLY REGULAR
MINUTES THE LAST TWO
SEASONS WHEN MEMPHIS
WAS TANKING.
ROB, WASHBURN.
THESE GUYS TOTALED 63
POINTS I THINK ON
MONDAY WHEN THEY
PLAYED.
THEY ALL RESTED
YESTERDAY.
NOW, CARTER WORTH
NOTING ACTUALLY JUST
GOT TRADED TO THE SUNS.
PROBABLY WON'T PLAY
BECAUSE THEY CAN'T
AFFORD HIM TO GET
INJURED.
THESE OTHER THREE GUYS
COMBINED FOR 34 POINTS.
THEY HAVE SO MUCH
EXPERIENCE COMPARED TO
THE CAVS WHO ARE
PLAYING A BUNCH OF
ROOKIES.
IT DOESN'T IMPACT THE
PROJECTION TOO MUCH TO
BE MORE LIKE MINUS 5.
WE'RE GETTING 2, 2 1/2
ON THE MARKET.
I'M GOING WITH THE
GRIZZLIES.
DOUG: DO YOU BELIEVE IN
REST DAYS IN VEGAS?
COME ON.
OR WAS THAT IN SALT
LAKE.
PRESTON: THIS ONE IS IN
SALT LAKE.
DOUG: FEWER
DISTRACTIONS, I WOULD
THINK.
>> YOU WOULD THINK.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
DOUG: PRESTON IS
PLAYING HOME COURT
ADVANTAGE.
HE IS OUT THERE IN LAS
VEGAS.
JOE, WHAT DO YOU GOT
FOR YOUR BEST BET?
JOE: THE SAN FRANCISCO
GIANTS AT PLUS 120 OVER
THE SAN DIEGO PADRES AS
THEY LOOK FOR THE SWEEP
TONIGHT.
THE GIANTS' BATS HAVE
COME ALIVE AS OF LATE.
THREE STRAIGHT WINS,
ALL OF WHICH HAVE
FEATURED TEN OR MORE
RUNS.
NOW, TONIGHT THE PADRES
WHO RANKED 19th AT OPS
ARE GOING TO FACE GIANT
RIGHT-HANDER SEAN
ANDERSON.
ANDERSON HAS BEEN THE
MOST CONSISTENT PITCHER
FOR THE GIANTS THIS
SEASON.
A LOT OF PEOPLE MAY
THINK THAT'S MADISON
BUMGARNER.
GO BACK TO JUNE 12th.
HE FACED THE PADRE
LINE-UP.
FOUR HITS, TWO EARNED
RUNS IN SIX INNINGS
PITCHED.
HE IS GOING TO TAKE THE
MOUND FOR THE GIANTS,
WHICH IS THE BIG EDGE
HERE.
HE IS EXTREMELY
UNDERVALUED.
FOR THE PADRES, IT'S
GOING TO BE THE
YOUNGSTER CALTRON.
THE RIGHTY AGAINST SAN
FRANCISCO.
IS HE COMING OUT OF THE
BULLPEN TO MAKE HIS
FIRST START IN A FEW
WEEKS.
SIX STARTS THIS SEASON.
HE HAS AN E.R.A. NORTH
OF FIVE.
18 EARNED RUNS AND JUST
31 INNINGS PITCHED.
I LIKE THE GIANTS TO
GET THE SWEEP TONIGHT,
AND THEN THEY'RE OFF
TOMORROW.
FIRST TIME OFF ON JULY
4th SINCE 1941.
GIANTS PLUS 120.
YOU CAN BOOK IT.
DOUG: GIANTS BATS HAVE
BEEN HOT IN SAN DIEGO.
WE HAVE PRESTON IN
VEGAS.
PICKING A SUMMER LEAGUE
GAME.
>> GRIZZLIES-GIANTS,
MARLINS.
JOE IN THE BAY AREA
TAKING THE GIANTS.
YOU GOING TO THE
TRI-STATE AREA FOR
YOURS?
STEVE: DARN RIGHT.
THE ALL MIGHTY YANKEES.
FIRST TIME SINCE 2013.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN.
DOUG: NO, SIR.
STEVE: BACK ON THE
MOUND FORT YANKEES.
TAKE THE YANKEES.
DOUG: HE IS THROWING
WELL LATELY.
YOU'RE STICKING TO THE
HOME TEAM, SO TO SPEAK.
I'M GOING WITH MY TEAM,
AND WHERE I'M GOING TO
BE THIS HOLIDAY
WEEKEND.
I'M GOING WITH THE
DODGERS.
LOOK, I GOT LUCKY LAST
NIGHT.
FIRST ONE --
STEVE: LUCKY?
DOUG: BEYOND LUCKY.
STEVE: I DON'T WANT TO
HEAR ABOUT THAT
ANYMORE.
NEVER AGAIN.
DOUG: IN AN EIGHT-START
STRETCH AN E.R.A. OF
1.64.
EIGHT STARTS.
THEN GOT TOUCHED UP THE
LAST ONE.
THAT WAS AT COORS
FIELD.
COORS FIELD.
DODGERS ARE HOT.
AMAZING HOME RECORD.
>> FIVE STRAIGHT WALKS
>> WE'RE GOING TO NEED
TO COVER
>> IT'S NEVER BEEN DONE
BEFORE
>> WE'RE GOING TO HOPE
NOT TO GET TO THE
BOTTOM OF THE NINTH.
WE NEED BREATHING ROOM,
BUT I DON'T THINK THAT
BUELLER IS GOING TO
GIVE UP MUCH.
I THINK THIS ONE GETS
AWAY FROM THE D-BACKS.
WHO KNOWS?
LOCKER ROOM DEMORALIZED
AFTER THAT?
BULLPEN CERTAINLY IS
SHAKY.
I'LL LAY THE ONE AND A
HALF.
I COULDN'T FIND ANY
OBSCENE MONEY LINES AND
PARLAY WITH THE DODGERS
STRAIGHT UP.
I WILL JUST LAY THE RUN
AND A HALF AND TRY TO
STAY HOT THIS WEEK.
STEVE LAYING THE $1.38
AS WELL.
ALL OF US PLAYING TO
OUR HOME TEAMS.
I LOVE IT.
JOE PLUS MONEY WITH THE
GIANTS AND THE
GRIZZLIES FOR PRESTON
OUT THERE.
I LOVE IT, SCOUTING FOR
PRESTON.
STEVE: I KNOW.
DOUG: GOLD CUP
SEMIFINALS TONIGHT.
MEN'S SOCCER FOR THE
AMERICANS AS THEY FACE
JAMAICA.
REMEMBER, THEY MET LAST
GOLD CUP FINAL IN 2017.
2-1 VICTORY FOR THE
AMERICANS.
THREE-WAY BETTING.
U.S. IS 190 MINUS $1.90
TO WIN IN REGULATION.
THE DRAW PLUS $2.75 AND
JAMAICA A HUGE UNDERDOG
WITH THE OVER-UNDER AT
2.50, AND THE UNDER IS
MINUS $1 .90.
FOR MORE LET'S GO OUT
TO NASHVILLE AHEAD OF
TONIGHT'S GAME AND
BRING IN ESPN-FC
REPORTER JEFF CARLISLE.
JEFF, APPRECIATE YOU
TAKING THE TIME.
U.S. FAVORITE AS YOU
WELL KNOW, BUT LET'S GO
BACK ABOUT A MONTH AGO
WHERE THEY LOST A
FRIENDLY TO JAMAICA
1-0.
HOW DOES THE TEAM
TONIGHT COMPARE TO THE
ONE THAT LOST THAT
GAME?
>> WELL, IT'S GOING TO
BE A VERY DIFFERENT
TEAM TO TAKE THE FIELD
FOR THE UNITED STATES
TONIGHT.
I COUNT AT LEAST SEVEN
DIFFERENT PLAYERS THAT
WILL BE IN THE STARTING
LINE-UP.
POSSIBLY EIGHT.
THOSE ARE KEY PLAYERS
AS WELL.
KEY ATTACKING PLAYERS
WHEN YOU ARE TALKING
ABOUT CHRISTIAN, WESLEY
McKINNEY.
THE FORWARD WILL BE
JOSIE ALTADORE.
NONE OF THE PLAYERS
PLAYED IN THAT GAME.
THEN YOU HAVE THE GUY
KIND OF PROVIDING THE
SHIELD IN FRONT OF THE
DEFENSE.
MICHAEL BRADLEY.
HE IS GOING TO BE A KEY
PLAYER FOR THE U.S.
TONIGHT.
HE IS GOING TO HAVE TO
PLAY VERY WELL, BE VERY
MOBILE, AND SO
OBVIOUSLY IT'S GOING TO
BE A VERY DIFFERENT
TEAM FOR THE U.S. TO
TAKE THE FIELD.
CONTRAST THAT WITH JAM
ACHE WHY.
THEY HAVE SEVEN PLAYERS
THAT TOOK THE FIELD IN
THE QUARTERFINAL
AGAINST PANAMA THAT
WERE ALSO ON THE FIELD
THAT NIGHT IN
WASHINGTON D.C. WHEN
THEY PLAYED THAT
FRIENDLY AGAINST THE
U.S.
JAMAICA IS GOING TO
HAVE A FEW NEW FACES.
THE U.S. WILL HAVE A
LOT OF NEW FACES.
DOUG: THE OVER-UNDER IS
TWO AND A HALF.
HOW MUCH SCORING DO YOU
EXPECT?
>> I DON'T EXPECT A
WHOET LOCAL OF SCORING
TONIGHT.
JAMAICA HAS ONLY
CONCEDED TWO GOALS IN
THE ENTIRE TOURNAMENT.
THE UNITED STATES HAS
KEPT A CLEAN SHEET IN
EVERY ONE OF THEIR GOLD
CUP GAMES.
THEIR DEFENSE HAS BEEN
VERY STOUT.
THE BACK LINE HAS BEEN
VERY CONSISTENT.
THEY'VE BEEN TESTED.
I MEAN, THE
QUARTERFINALS WITH
COURASAO.
THEY HAD GOOD CHANCES
AS WELL, AND JACK'S
GOAL HAS BEEN VERY,
VERY GOOD.
ON THE OTHER HAND, YOU
HAVE ANDRE BLAKE.
HE PLAYS FOR THE
PHILADELPHIA UNION.
HE IS ALSO VERY GOOD
AND CAME UM UP BIG A
COUPLE OF TIMES IN THAT
QUARTERFINAL WIN OVER
PANAMA.
I DON'T EXPECT A WHOLE
LOT OF SCORING TONIGHT.
I EXPECT IT TO BE A
TIGHT SEMIFINAL LIKE
LAST NIGHT WITH MEXICO
AND HAITI.
AGAIN, TWO AND A HALF
GOALS SEEMS LIKE A LOT
TO ME.
I EXPECT IT TO BE A 1
-0 AFFAIR FOR SURE.
DOUG: IN FAVOR OF WHO?
>> THE UNITED STATES.
I WOULD AGREE THAT THE
UNITED STATES ARE
SLIGHT FAVORITES, BUT,
AGAIN, JAMAICA HAS
PLAYED THEM VERY TOUGH,
AND JAMAICA HAS GONE
DEEP IN THIS
TOURNAMENT, YOU KNOW,
THE LAST TWO EDITIONS.
THEY'VE MADE THE FINALS
TWO TIMES.
WHEN IT COMES TO THE
GOLD CUP, JAMAICA IS A
DIFFICULT TEAM TO BREAK
DOWN.
I SEE THE U.S. GETTING
THROUGH TONIGHT.
DOUG: SOUNDS GOOD.
JEFF CARLISLE JOINING
US FROM NASHVILLE HEAD
OF TONIGHT'S GOLD CUP
SEMIFINAL.
THANK YOU, JEFF.
JEFF: YOU'RE WELCOME.
DOUG: CONTINUING TO
COVER A WIDE RANGE OF
SPORTS COMING UP NEXT.
THE NUMBER ONE GOLFER
IN THE WORLD.
BROOKS KOEPKA IS YOUR
FAVORITE AT THE 3M
OPEN, AND WE'LL TELL
YOU WHY HE IS NOT THE
BEST BET.
PLUS, JOEY CHESTNUT, A
HEAVY FAVORITE IN THE
HOT DOG EATING CONTEST,
BUT OUR EXPERTS WILL
TELL YOU WHY WEATHER
COULD BE A BIG FACTOR
IN THE OVER-UNDER OF
HOT DOG EATING.
THAT'S NEXT.
My insurance rates are probably
gonna double.
But dad, you've got
ALLSTATE.
WITH ACCIDENT FORGIVENESS
THEY GUARANTEE YOUR RATES
WON'T GO UP
JUST BECAUSE OF AN ACCIDENT.
Smart kid.
INDEED.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
♪♪
Lower carbs.
Lower calories.
♪♪
Higher expectations.
The light beer you've
been waiting for
has arrived.
Corona Premier.
It's time for our Lowest
Prices of the Season on
the Sleep Number 360 smart bed.
It senses your movement
and automatically adjusts
to keep you both comfortable.
The queen Sleep Number 360
c4 smart bed, now $1299.
Plus, free premium delivery
when you add a base.
Ends Sunday.
Look! Make a wish!
I wish for a Biggie
Bag from Wendy's.
I wish everyone loved each
other and was always...
That's a great wish, Jimmy.
Get a Bacon Double stack with
a quarter pound of fresh beef,
nuggets, fries and a
drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
Coach! It's kinda hard to see
the ball.
I've been there.
I had a TV service with hardly
any sports in 4K.
Couldn't see any of the quality
details.
I switched to DIRECTV, now I get
the most live sports in 4K.
So how does that help me?
It really doesn't.
I don't know why I told you
that. Go get 'em sport!
Live sports that aren't in 4K
are just kinda TV.
Don't just kinda TV. DIRECTV
Don't have 4K? Call
1.855.WATCH.4K and ask for it
today.
DODOUG: TIME FOR DAILY
DIAMOND DOG, AND THE
BEST PART IS THE DOG WE
GET TO FEATURE.
THIS IS BAXTER, WHO IS
A SERVICE DOG HERE AT
ESPN.
WORKS WITH OUR AUDIO
ENGINEER TYLER.
YOU REQUEST SEE BAXTER
CERTAINLY IN CHARGE,
AND HE IS NOW
RESPONSIBLE FOR HITTING
THE BLEEP BUTTON
WHENEVER I LOSE A BET
ON SET.
BAXTER IS PROFILED AS
WE TAKE A LOOK AT THE
BIGGEST UNDERDOGS OF
THE NIGHT, AND THE
BIGGEST ONE IS ACTUALLY
A HOME TEAM.
THE BLUE JAYS IN
TORONTO FACING CHRIS
SALE AND THE RED SOX.
D-BACKS ABOVE 200 ON
THE COMEBACK FACING THE
DODGERS AND WALKER
BUELLER, AS I NOTED
EARLIER, AND THE
MARLINS DID CLOSE
AROUND PLUS 240 AGAINST
THE NATS, BUT FIRST
PITCH ALREADY UNDERWAY
AT 6:05.
JOE BACK WITH ME.
WHAT'S YOUR DIAMOND DOG
TONIGHT, JOE?
>> ALL RIGHT, DOUG.
LIMITED OPTIONS
TONIGHT, AND THERE IS
NO WAY I WANT TO GET IN
FRONT OF THE WALKER
BUELLER TRAIN.
WE'RE GOING TO FADE
CHRIS SALE AND THE RED
SOX.
GIVE ME TORONTO PLUS
240.
CHRIS SALE BROKE FROM
THE GATE IN SLUGGISH
FASHION.
A LOT OF PEOPLE
WONDERING WHAT WENT
WRONG.
SETTLE DOWN.
IT WAS OUTSTANDING.
AS OF LATE, A BILL
IFFY.
NOT TERRIBLE, BUT IFFY.
THE LAST THREE STARTS
HE HAS GIVEN UP TEN
EARNED RUNS OVER 17
INNINGED PITCHED.
AGAIN, NOT TERRIBLE,
BUT MAYBE THERE'S
SOMETHING THERE WE CAN
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IN
THIS SITUATION.
ONE OF THOSE STARTS WAS
AT FENWAY AGAINST
TORONTO.
GAVE UP A FEW RUNS.
DIDN'T EXACTLY WORK
THAT DEEP INTO THE
GAME.
THIS MAY BE A SPOT WE
CAN TAKE ADVANTAGE OF
CHRIS SALE, WHO, BY THE
WAY, THIS IS THE WORST
HARD-HIT PERCENTAGE OF
HIS ENTIRE CAREER.
HIS FAST BALL IS DOWN
ABOUT A FULL MILE AN
HOUR OVER HIS RESULTS
FROM LAST SEASON.
NOT THE GUY WE SAW LAST
SEASON.
STILL A VERY GOOD
PITCHER.
BOSTON HAS LOST FIVE OF
EIGHT, SO THIS COULD BE
A NICE LITTLE
OPPORTUNITY HERE TO
BACK THE DOG AT PLUS
240.
DOUG: I CAN'T FAULT YOU
THERE GIVEN THE PRICE
ON THE DOG.
I'M GOING TO GO WITH
THE ROYALS PLUS 145.
A LITTLE BIT OF A --
GOING HIGHER.
IN TWO STARTS SINCE
RETURNING FROM INJURY
MIKE LEVINGER HAS
ALLOWED 12 RUNS.
SURE LOOKS LIKE HE
RETURNED TOO QUIBBLE
ARE FROM THAT BACK
INJURY.
SOMETHING DOESN'T SEEM
RIGHT.
I'LL TAKE THE ROYALS AT
HOME, PLUS THE JUICE
THERE.
BY THE WAY, IF YOU WANT
TO SEND IN YOUR DOG, WE
WILL PROFILE HIM, EVERY
TIME WE HAVE THIS
SEGMENT.
TWEET ME@DOUG ESPN.
ONE FINAL LOOK AT
BAXTER IN CHARGE.
HOW AWESOME.
PGA TOUR HEADING TO
MINNESOTA.
NO SURPRISE, BROOKS
KOEPKA, YOUR FAVORITE
AT 8-1.
THE ONLY PLAYER WITH
SINGLE DIGIT ODDS.
THAT'S FOLLOWED BY
JASON DAY AND
MATSUYAMA.
11-1 A PIECE.
15-1.
NOT POSTED HERE.
LEFTY, PHIL MICKELSON
AT 40-1.
LET'S WELCOME BACK
ANITA MARKS HERE TO
TALK A LITTLE GOLF
GIVEN IT IS A
WEDNESDAY.
OF THE FAVORITES,
ANITA, WHICH ONE GRABS
YOUR ATTENTION?
ANITA: 27 WATER
HAZARDSES, 24 BUNKERS.
THAT'S WHAT THESE GUIDE
HAVING FACING, AND
DECKY HAS BEEN COMING
IN RED HOT THIS SEASON.
HE HAS NOT MISSED A
CUT, DOUG.
NOT ONE ALL SEASON
LONG.
HE IS IN GREAT FORM.
HE IS RED HOT WITH HIS
IRONS, AND EACH AND
EVERY WEEK WE TALK
ABOUT THE ANALYTICS
THAT'S GOING TO PLAY
WELL ON THIS COURSE.
BIRDIE AVERAGE.
HE RANKS TENTH ON TOUR.
PAR FIVE SCORING.
HE RANKS 25th AND ALSO
STROKES GAINED, TEE TO
GREEN, HE RANKS FOURTH
ON TOUR.
HE IS UP THERE.
TOP 25 IN HIS CATEGORY.
HE IS GOING TO DO
EXCEPTIONALLY WELL.
I LIKE HIM.
I'M PUTTING SOME
HARD-EARNED MONEY ON
HIM.
DOUG: YOU LIKED HIM
LAST WEEK.
DID WELL.
WHAT IS ANOTHER GOLFER
THAT YOU THINK KIND OF
GRABS YOUR ATTENTION IN
TERMS OF VALUE?
ANITA: PATRICK REEVES.
HE IS COMING IN TIED
FOR FIFTH LAST WEEK.
HE IS COMING IN HOT,
AND HE IS COMING IN
WITH A LOT OF
CONFIDENCE.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT WHAT
HE HAS BEEN ABLE TO DO,
THE HISTORY IN
MINNESOTA, LET'S GO
BACK TO THE 2016 ROOID
ESH CUP WHERE HE GOT
THAT NAME CAPTAIN
AMERICA BECAUSE HE TOOK
WORRY TO THE LIMIT.
HIS PUTTING IS A LOT
BETTER, AND EACH AND
EVERY WEEK WE LIKE TO
TALK ABOUT THE GRASS.
IT'S BENT GRASS THIS
WEEK.
THE GREENS AREN'T GOING
TO BE AS DIFFICULT AS
SOME OF THESE GUYS HAVE
SEEN IN PREVIOUS WEEKS.
I LIKE PATRICK REED.
DOUG: FIRE AWAY HERE.
ANITA: AS ALWAYS, THE
TWO GUYS THAT I FIRST
TALK ABOUT, MY LONG,
SHORT ODDS, LIKE TO
PLAY THEM IN DFS AS
WELL.
I'M GOING WITH DEKI AND
PATRICK.
DECHAMBEAUX.
HIS PUTTING IS FINALLY
COMING BACK, AND HE
DOES WELL WITH GENEROUS
FAIRWAYS, AND THAT'S
WHAT HE WILL SEE
STARTING TOMORROW.
NEIMAN, BACK-TO-BACK
TOP FIVES.
HIS NEW PUTTING
PRACTICE THAT HE HAS
BEEN PRACTICING WITH,
AND IT'S REALLY BEEN
HELPING HIM.
ALSO, 311st STROKES
GAINED TEE TO GREEN.
HOMA, THIS GUY MAKES
EVERY CUT.
48th PAR FIVE SCORING,
AND HERE'S THE THING.
THREE PAR FIVES, 593
YARDS, 596 YARDS.
THERE'S SOME LONG PAR
FIVES, AND REDMAN IS
COMING IN RED HOT AS
WELL.
SECOND LAST WEEK WITH
19 UNDER ON THE
TOURNAMENT.
THIS IS HIS THIRD PGA
START, AND THIS VERY
WELL COULD BE IF HE
WINS, THIS VERY WELL
COULD BE THE FOURTH
STRAIGHT WEEK ON THE
PGA TOUR THAT WE HAVE
THESE REALLY SURPRISING
GREAT WINNERS, SO I'M
ALWAYS ABOUT THAT.
I LOVE THE UNDER DOG.
I LOVE THE UNEXPECTED,
SO I'M REALLY, REALLY,
REALLY CHEERING FOR
REDMAN.
>> SOUNDS GOOD.
ANITA, THANKS FOR THE
INSIGHT.
ENJOY YOUR HOLIDAY, AND
YOU'LL BE BACK
OBVIOUSLY ON THE SHOW
ON FRIDAY.
ANITA: YES.
I'LL BE IN FOR YOU.
HOPEFULLY YOU HAVE A
GREAT WEEKEND.
DOUG: I WILL.
AND STRAIGHT AHEAD ON
THIS SHOW, THE GREATEST
EMCEE IN SHORTS, GEORGE
SHAY, WILL BREAK DOWN
TOMORROW'S HOT DOG
EATING CONTEST.
>> TO ME THAT'S THE
GREATEST HONOR OF THIS
SPORT IS TO BE ABLE TO
INTRODUCE JOEY CHESTNUT
BECAUSE TO ME HE IS
AMERICA ITSELF.
TO ME HE IS FREEDOM.
HE IS THE ESSENCE OF
WHO WE ARE.
[ dogs barking ]
What about him?
Let's do it.
[ sniffing ]
Come on.
This summer, add a new
member to the family.
Hurry into the Mercedes-Benz
Summer Event today
for exceptional offers.
Lease the GLC 300 SUV
for just $419 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz Summer
Event. Going on now.
DOUG: THE CHAMPIONSHIP
IS SET FOR THE WOMEN'S
WORLD CUP.
OBVIOUSLY, THE
AMERICANS ADVANCE.
TODAY NETHERLANDS GET
THE 99th MINUTE.
1-0.
THAT IS YOUR SHOWDOWN,
AND CEASAR'S JUST
POSTING THESE ODDS.
THE AMERICANS MINUS 475
TO HOIST THE TROPHY.
NOW, THREE-WAY BETTING
WILL BE OUT LATER.
JUST NO MATTER WHEN IT
OCCURS, U.S. NEARLY A
5-1 FAVORITE OVER
NETHERLANDS.
THAT IS SUNDAY.
LET'S GET READY FOR
TOMORROW.
IT IS A STAPLE ON OUR
INDEPENDENCE DAY.
THE NATHAN'S HOT DOG
EATING CONTEST.
>> AND HERE IS --
>> THROUGH MEDITATION,
HE LEARNED THAT HIS
SPIRIT ANIMAL IS A
BALONEY SANDWICH.
HE HAS THE BODY OF A --
AND THE EATING HABITS
OF HOMER SIMPSON.
HE IS NOT BOOKMARKED.
IF YOU ASKED HIM TO
NAME A COUNTRY IN
CENTRAL AMERICA, HE
WILL SAY KANSAS?
THE DIFFICULTY IN HIS
MARRIAGE BEGAN AFTER HE
NAMED HIS CHILDREN
MILD, MEDIUM, AND HOT.
HIS GOOD CHOLESTEROL IS
LOW.
HIS BAD CHOLESTEROL IS
HIGH.
AND HIS BMI IS
BORDERLINE
PRESIDENTIAL.
WHEN WE ARE YOUNG, WE
DRINK OUR COFFEE WITH
MILK AND SUGAR, AND AS
WE AGE WE DRINK IT WITH
MILK ONLY.
THEN WE DRINK IT BLACK.
THEN WE DRINK IT DECAF.
THEN WE DIE.
OUR NEXT SCENERY IS AT
DECAF.
IT IS AN HONOR TO ALL
THOSE NEW LIVING TO
BEHOLD THIS MAN.
HE IS THE -- CENTER OF
OUR NATION
>> ONE NATION, UNDER
GOD, INDIF IZIBLE
>> HE IS CHAMPION.
JOEY CHESTNUT!
DOUG: WE ARE NOW
PLEASED TO WELCOME IN
THE VOICE AND THE
BIGGEST PERSONALITY OF
THE JULY 4th HOT DOG
EATING CONTEST, GEORGE
SHAY.
GEORGE, THANKS SO MUCH
FOR TAKING THE TIME.
LET'S GET INTO IT.
JOEY CHESTNUT.
HE IS A RECORD 11
MUSTARD BELTS.
IS THERE ANY CHANCE HE
DOES NOT WIN THIS
EVENT?
>> OH, I THINK THERE'S
ABSOLUTELY A CHANCE HE
DOESN'T WIN, BUT I
THINK THE ODDS WOULD BE
EXTREMELY LOW.
NOT ONLY IS HE DOMINANT
IN THIS SPORT.
74 HOT DOGS AND BUNS
LAST YEAR IN TEN
MINUTES.
ON TOP OF THAT I SAW
HIM TODAY.
HE LOOKS ABSOLUTELY IN
TOP FORM.
HE IS VERY TRIM, VERY
FIT.
HE IS VERY HEALTHY AND
REST AND CONFIDENT.
I THINK HE IS GOING TO
BE COMING IN STRONG,
BUT AT ANY TIME HE
COULD BE BEATEN, AND
THERE ARE A COUPLE OF
GUYS.
JEFF AND MATT COULD
TAKE HIM DOWN.
DOUG: TALK MORE ABOUT
THOSE TWO KIND OF
CONTENDERS, IF YOU
WILL.
WHAT MAKES THEM --
WHAT'S THE PATH TO
THEIR SUCCESS AND
BEATING JOEY CHESTNUT?
>> WELL, BOTH OF THEM
HAVE ENORMOUS CAPACITY,
AND JEFFREY ESPER HAD
BEATEN JOEY CHESTNUT,
IF I'M CORRECT, TWO
TIMES IN THE LAST THREE
WEEKS.
HE GOT HIM IN HOSTESS,
AND HE GOT HIM IN
CHICKEN WINGS.
HE IS A MONSTER.
HE IS A RELATIVE
ROOKIE.
SECOND, THIRD YEAR ON
THE CIRCUIT.
I THINK HE GETS A
LITTLE BIT OF THE
JITTERS GOING INTO THE
BIG CONTEST ON THE
FOURTH OF JULY.
HE ATE 51 HOT DOGS TO
QUALIFY.
KEEP IN MIND, THE
QUALIFYING HOT DOGS ARE
HARDER TO EAT.
YOU REALLY HAVE TO
THINK OF HIM UP AT A 60
MARK OR SO.
THEN THERE'S ALSO MATT
STONY.
HE IS REALLY AN
INTERNET STAR NOW.
A YOUTUBE STAR.
DOUG: A COUPLE OF
THINGS TO DIGEST.
FORGIVE THE PUN.
QUALIFYING HOT DOGS ARE
HARDER TO EAT.
WHY IS THAT?
>> WELL, IF YOU THINK
OF IT -- YOU ARE AT
NATHAN'S, THE MECCA OF
HOT DOGS, AND THEY'RE
COOKED PERFECTLY COOKED
ON THE GRITLE, AND
THEY'RE COOKED TO COME
OFF A FEW MINUTES PRIOR
TO THE CONTEST.
THEY'RE THE PERFECT
TEMPERATURE.
THEY'RE WARM.
THEY'RE NOT COLD OR
HOT.
WHEN YOU ARE OUT THE
CIRCUIT, YOU MIGHT BE
AT A BALLPARK.
THEY'RE BRINGING THE
HOT DOGS IN IN WARMERS.
THEY'VE BEEN COOKED A
HALF AN HOUR, AN HOUR
BEFORE.
SOMETIMES THEY'RE NOT
FULLY GRITLED.
THEY'RE JUST COOKED OR
THEY'RE STEAMED, BUT
NOT GRILLED AS THEY
WOULD BE AT CONEY
ISLAND, AND AS A
RESULT, THEY'RE MORE
DIFFICULT TO EAT.
OR IT TAKES LONGER TO
EAT THOSE DOGS.
FASCINATING STUFF.
CHESTNUT EIGHT ATE 72
HOT DOGS.
DO YOU SEE HIM GOING
PAST THAT MARK AS WELL
THIS YEAR?
>> I ABSOLUTELY THINK
HE WILL BE AROUND
THERE.
THERE HAVE BEEN TIMES
WHEN THINGS DROP OFF.
IT COULD BE THE
TEMPERATURE OF THE DAY.
IT COULD BE LITERALLY
THE HUMIDITY.
ACTUALLY, WHEN YOU HAVE
A VERY, VERY DRY DAY,
IT CAN DRY OUT THE
BUNS, SO EVEN IF
THEY'RE ONLY OUT THERE
FOR FIVE OR TEN
MINUTES, THEY HAVE A
DIFFERENT CONSISTENCY.
THE HOT DOGS CAN
TIGHTEN UP MORE.
THE TEMPERATURE COULD
PLAY A ROLE.
DOUG: MICKEY GOING FOR
A SIXTH STRAIGHT
MUSTARD BELT.
WHAT ARE THE CHANCES IN
YOUR EYES SHE DOES NOT
MAKE IT SIX STRAIGHT?
>> I THINK THEY'RE LOW.
THE CHANCES THAT SHE
DOES NOT WIN.
YOU KNOW, SHE -- THERE
COULD BE MORE
VARIABILITY IN HER
PERFORMANCE ON THAT.
DUG THE WHOLE SPECTACLE
IS AWESOME.
I LOOK FORWARD TO WATCH
IT ON JULY 4th.
IT WAS AN HONOR TO HAVE
YOU HERE.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO
WATCHING YOUR
PERFORMANCE AS WELL.
THANK YOU FOR TAKING
THE TIME?
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING
ME.
DOUG: AND ON THAT NOTE,
WE GO TO PROP CULTURE
TO WRAP UP THE SHOW.
JOE JOINS ME NOW.
JOE, LOOK, TOTAL OF HOT
DOGS ON THE MEN'S
DIVISION, 73 1/2, AND
THIS IS INTERESTING.
I LOVE WHAT EMMY GEORGE
SHAY JUST SAID ABOUT
MATT STONY, WHO HE IS
HEARING GRUMBLINGS THAT
HE IS GOING TO REALLY
BRING IT THIS YEAR, AND
ENORMOUS CAPACITY.
I HAVE BEEN TRACKING
THIS STUFF FOR A LONG
TIME WHEN I WORKED IN
LAS VEGAS.
I GOT TO DO A LIVE SHOT
DOWNTOWN WITH THE ONE
AND ONLY JOEY CHESTNUT
AND THE ONE AND ONLY
KOBAYASHI.
THEY WERE TALKING TRASH
TO ONE ANOTHER.
A LOT OF FUN.
I'M NO EXPERT, BUT I'M
STAYING UNDER 73 1/2 IF
I HAD TO, JOE.
JOE: SHADES OF DAVIS
FROST AND RICHARD
NIXON, NO DOUBT.
NOW, I'M GOING OVER
73 1/2 HOT DOGS, AND I
GOT JOEY CHESTNUT
WINNING THIS THING.
JOEY CHESTNUT LIVES
HERE IN THE BAY AREA
WHERE I LIVE.
THE LAND OF KALE.
THE LAND OF AVOCADO
TOAST, SODA TAXES.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT
HAVING A CHEESEBURGER,
THEY WANT TO CAST YOU
OUT.
BEAUTIFUL AREA, NO
DOUBT, BUT THEY ARE NOT
TOO FOND OF NASHING
73 1/2 HOT DOGS IN TEN
MINUTES.
THAT'S NOT HOW PEOPLE
DO THINGS HERE, AND,
YET, JOEY CHESTNUT
RISES EVERY DAY IN THE
FACE OF THAT ADVERSITY,
AND HE TAKES ON HIS
DETRACTORS.
LET'S GO BACK TO 20 IS
A WHEN HE LOST TO MATT
STONY.
62 TO 60.
CAME BACK THE NEXT YEAR
TO SET A RECORD WITH 70
HOT DOGS.
CAME BACK THE FOLLOWING
YEAR TO SET A RECORD
WITH 72 HOT DOGS AND
THEN CAME BACK LAST
YEAR TO SET ANOTHER
RECORD WITH 74 HOT
DOGS.
THIS GUY IS NOT WORRIED
ABOUT HIS COMPETITION.
HE IS WORRIED ABOUT
HISTORY, AND HE HAS
STATED THAT HIS GOAL IS
TO KNOCK DOWN 80 HOT
DOGS IN A SINGLE
SITTING.
DOUG, I THINK TO YOU,
GOD BLESS JOEY
CHESTNUT.
GOD BLESS AMERICA.
DOUG: AND WEATHER ON
YOUR SIDE, JOE.
IT'S GOING TO BE A
HUMID DAY, AND GEORGE
SHAY WAS JUST SAYING
THAT THAT LENDS ITSELF
TO THE OVER BECAUSE THE
BUNS WON'T DRY OUT.
THEN I DIDN'T THINK OF
ASKING HIM A LOT OF THE
COMPETITORS DIP THE BUN
IN THE WATER, SO I'M A
LITTLE CONFUSED.
I HAVE CERTAIN
THRESHOLDS FOR
EXPERTISE ON THE HOT
DOG EATING CONTEST.
I DO KNOW THAT I WILL
BE WATCHING, AND THIS
ISN'T LIKE THOSE OTHER
SPORTS LIKE FOOTBALL --
THEY ONLY WATCHED THE
LAST FEW MINUTES.
YOU HAVE TO WATCH THE
BEGINNING BECAUSE OF
GEORGE SHAY AND ALL THE
INTRODUCTIONS AND THE
POMP AND CIRCUMSTANCE
AS WELL.
JOE, WE APPRECIATE IT.
I KNOW WHO YOU ARE
ROOTING FOR HERE.
YOUR HOMETOWN GUY, AND
MORE IMPORTANTLY, HAPPY
FOURTH OF JULY AND
ENJOY YOUR HOLIDAY, MY
FRIEND.
AND RECAPPING OUR BEST
BETS, PRESTON, THE
VEGAS GRIZZLIES MINUS
2.50.
JOE ON THE UNDERDOG
GIANTS PLUS 1.20.