IT RIGHT WAS THE SQUAD ITSELF.
AFTER THE GAME, THEY POASTD A
VIDEO OF MOST OF THE TEAM
DANCING TO THE 2007 BANGER.
IF YOU DON'T KNOW IT, THAT
SUCKS FOR YOU.
BUT THE FACT THAT THIS SONG IS
WHAT BRINGS THIS TEAM TOGETHER
IS AMAZING.
IN THE NAME OF THE GROUP WHO
MADE IT, PROBABLY DESCRIBED
BOTH COUNTRIES' HISTORIES OF
MONEY MAKING QUITE WELL, CRIME
MOB.
GOD BLESS THEM, AND GOD BLESS
AMERICA.
"NFL LIVE" IS NEXT.
WE'RE BACK ON JULY 11.
♪♪
>>> "NFL LIVE" PACKED WITH
SPECIAL GUEST STARS TODAY.
JAGUARS QUARTERBACK JALEN RAMSEY
JOINS THE SHOW LIVE.
TALK ABOUT HOW THE JAGS BOUNCE
BACK THIS YEAR.
WE'LL TALK TO BROWNS TIGHT END
DAVID NJOKU ABOUT THE EXCITEMENT
IN CLEVELAND AND WHAT'S AHEAD
FOR THE BROWNS.
SINCE TOMORROW IS INDEPENDENCE
DAY, WE'LL SHOW YOU SOME OF OF
THE BEST INDEPENDENT PLAYS IN
NFL HISTORY.
YOU'LL WANT TO STICK AROUND TO
FIND OUT IF ONLY WHAT YOU
NEED -- IF YOU CAN'T GET YOUR
HOLIDAY WEEKEND STARTED WITHOUT
HEARING 90 MORE MINUTES OF
OFF-SEASON CONTENT, YOU HAVE
COME TO THE RIGHT PLACE.
DAVE GRAZIANO HERE.
WE'LL START WITH THE SITUATION
REGARDING EZEKIEL ELLIOTT.
THE COWBOYS SUPERSTAR RUNNING
BACK MET TUESDAY WITH ROGER
GOODELL TO DISCUSS A RECENT
INCIDENT INVOLVING ELLIOTT AND A
SECURITY GUARD IN LAS VEGAS.
ELLIOTT WAS DETAINED BUT NOT
ARRESTED.
GIVEN HIS HISTORY WITH THE
PERSONAL CONDUCT POLICY, THE
COMMISSIONER CALLED HIM IN FOR A
DISCUSSION.
FOLLOWING THAT DISCUSSION,
ELLIOTT POSTED THE FOLLOWING
STATEMENT ON TWITTER.
EARLIER TODAY I MET WITH THE
COMMISSIONER TO SHARE WITH HIM
WHAT OCCURRED IN LAS VEGAS AND
WHAT I HAVE LEARNED FROM THAT
INCIDENT.
I'VE WORKED HARD TO MAKE BETTER
DECISIONS AND LIVE UP TO THE
HIGH STANDARDS EXPECTED OF ME.
I FAILED TO DO THAT HERE AND I
MADE A POOR DECISION.
I APOLOGIZED TO KYLE JOHNSON,
THAT'S THE SECURITY GUARD IN
QUESTION AT THE TIME AND I MEANT
IT.
I NEED TO WORK HARDER TO ENSURE
I DO NOT PUT MYSELF IN
COMPROMISED SITUATIONS IN THE
FUTURE.
I AM REDEDICATING MYSELF TO USE
ALL THE RESOURCES THE LEAGUE HAS
MADE AVAILABLE.
IN THE END, IT'S UP TO ME AND I
AM DETERMINED NOT TO BE IN THIS
POSITION AGAIN.
WHY IS THIS A BIG DEAL?
PARTIALLY BECAUSE OF THE WARNING
COMMISSIONER ROGER GOODELL
ISSUED TO ELLIOTT WHEN HE
SUSPENDED HIM IN 2017.
IN HIS SUSPENSION LETTER AT THAT
TIME, GOODELL WROTE TO ELLIOTT,
YOU MUST HAVE NO FURTHER ADVERSE
INVOLVEMENT WITH LAW ENFORCEMENT
AND MUST NOT COMMIT ANY
ADDITIONAL VIOLATIONS OF LEAGUE
POLICY.
YOU SHOULD UNDERSTAND THAT
ANOTHER VIOLATION MAY RESULT IN
YOUR SUSPENSION OR POTENTIAL
BANISHMENT FROM THE NFL.
LOOK, WE'RE NOT HERE TO MAKE
EQUATIONS OR COMPARISONS TO WHAT
HE DID IN THE PAST AND WHAT HE
DID NOW.
HERE HE IS MAKING THE WRONG
HEADLINES AGAIN.
BEING CALLED INTO THE
COMMISSIONER'S OFFICE, NO SMALL
THING FOR A PLAYER IN HIS
SITUATION.
MIKE, IF YOU'RE IN THE FRONT
OFFICE OF THIS TEAM AND YOU HAVE
A PLAYER IN THIS SITUATION, GOT
THE CONTRACT SITUATION COMING UP
OVER THE NEXT COUPLE OF YEARS,
WHAT KIND OF CONVERSATION DO YOU
NEED TO HAVE WITH HIM AT THIS
TIME.
>> YOU NEED TO HAVE A DIRECT,
HONEST AND VERY DIFFICULT
CONVERSATION.
YOU HAVE TO LET HIM KNOW THAT
THIS BEHAVIOR IS UNACCEPTABLE
AND THIS IS MORE THAN ONE
INSTANCE.
AS YOU SAID, DAN, MAYBE IT'S NOT
AS SIGNIFICANT AS THE ONE THAT
HAPPENED IN THE PAST, BUT FROM
THE COWBOY ORGANIZATION, I WOULD
TELL HIM, LOOK WE'RE GOING TO
HIT PAUSE ON YOUR CONTRACT
NEGOTIATIONS.
THERE'S FOUR OTHER PLAYERS RIGHT
NOW THAT THE COWBOYS HAVE, DAK
PRESCOTT, THEIR STARTING
QUARTERBACK, AMARI COOPER WHO
THEY TRADED FOR FROM THE OAKLAND
RAIDERS, JAYLEN SMITH AND BYRON
JONES.
ALL FOUR OF THOSE PLAYERS ARE
GOING FOR THE LAST YEAR OF THEIR
RESPECTIVE CONTRACTS.
THEY HAVE PLAYED WELL AND ACTED
FLAWLESSLY OFF THE FIELD.
I HAVE HAD THAT CONVERSATION
WITH EZEKIEL ELLIOTT TO SAY
WHILE WE APPRECIATE WHAT YOU'VE
DONE ON THE FIELD, RIGHT NOW
YOU'RE UNDER CONTRACT FOR THIS
YEAR.
WE HAVE THE OPTION FOR 2020 AND
WE CAN FRANCHISE YOU THE YEAR
AFTER.
BASICALLY FOR THE NEXT THREE
YEARS WE CAN CONTROL YOUR
RIGHTS.
BECAUSE OF THE WAY YOU'VE ACTED,
WE'RE HITTING PAUSE AROUND IT
MAY NOT BE WHAT YOU WANT TO
HEAR, BUT THAT'S THE
CONVERSATION YOU NEED TO HAVE
WITH THE PLAYER.
>> STANDPOINT OF A TEAMMATE, A
GUY LIKE THIS IN THIS SITUATION,
WHAT CONVERSATION DO YOU HAVE?
>> LISTEN, I THINK IT'S
IMPORTANT THAT YOU'RE AVAILABLE.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, IF THE
GUY WHO BASICALLY STIRS THE
DRINK ISN'T AVAILABLE, YOU'RE
AFFECTING MY MONEY.
YOU'RE AFFECTING EVERYBODY IN
THE ORGANIZATION.
THINK ABOUT IT.
JASON GARRETT, THIS IS LIKE HIS
CONTRACT YEAR, THIS IS HIS YEAR,
DO OR DIE YEAR AND YOU'RE
PUTTING YOURSELF -- YOU'RE
EZEKIEL ELLIOTT, YOU'RE PUTTING
YOURSELF IN A COMPROMISING
SITUATION WHERE YOU COULD BE
POTENTIALLY SUSPENDED ACHBD NOT
AVAILABLE TO THE TEAM.
THERE'S SO MUCH RIDING ON THE
DALLAS COWBOYS THIS YEAR, IT'S
ALL HANDS ON DECK.
IF I'M A VETERAN IN THE LOCKER
ROOM, LIKE, DUDE, LET'S CHILL
OUT, CALM DOWN, CAN'T KEEP
PUTTING YOURSELF OUT THERE
BECAUSE YOU'RE HURTING
EVERYBODY, NOT JUST YOURSELF.
>> DAMIAN, TO YOUR POINT HOW
EZEKIEL ELLIOTT STIRS THE DRINK.
LOOK AT DAK PRESCOTT, HE HAS A
PASSER RATING OF 122 WHEN IT'S
PLAY ACTION, THE REASON IT'S
EFFECTIVE IS THE OPPOSING
DEFENSE IS WORRYING ABOUT
EZEKIEL ELLIOTT.
THAT IS NOT BY COINCIDENCE THAT
HAS A HIGH PASSING RATING WHEN
THEY'RE IN PLAY ACTION.
BECAUSE EVERYTHING WILL BE KEYED
ON EZEKIEL ELLIOTT.
IF HE'S NOT AVAILABLE -- AMARI
COOPER WAS A VERY VALUABLE
ACQUISITION.
WITHOUT EZEKIEL ELLIOTT, THAT
OFFENSE IS A LOT EASIER TO
DEFEND.
>> NO QUESTION OBVIOUSLY ABOUT
THE IMPORTANCE OF EZEKIEL
ELLIOTT TO THE COWBOYS OFFENSE,
THEY STRUGGLED WITHOUT HIM IN
2017 WHEN HE WAS SUSPENDED.
WE AWAIT WORD FROM THE
COMMISSIONER'S OFFICE WHETHER HE
FACES DISCIPLINE FOR THIS
INCIDENT.
IF THAT COMES IN THE NEXT HOUR
AND A HALF, WE'LL BRING IT TO
YOU.
IN THE MEANTIME, WE'RE GOING TO
MOVE ON TO THE SILLIER PORTION
OF YOUR SHOW.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THE 243rd ANNIVERSARY OF THE
SIGNING OF DECLARATION OF
INDEPENDENCE.
WE DIDN'T HAVE ACCESS TO THOMAS
JEFFERSON, WE HAVE DAMIAN WOODY
AND MIKE TANNENBAUM.
EVEN THOUGH THEY MAY NOT HAVE
BEEN THE FIRST CHOICE ON
DECLARATION, JEFFERSON COULDN'T
MAKE IT, WE'VE DECIDED TO ASK
THEM FOR DECLARATIONS OF THEIR
OWN.
WHAT THIS IS GOING TO BE IS
SOMETHING YOU FEEL STRONGLY
ABOUT, SOMETHING YOU FEEL LIKE
DECLARING ABOUT THE UPCOMING NFL
SEASON.
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE ABOUT
LIFE, LIBERTY OR THE PURSUIT OF
APP HAPPINESS.
IT HAS TO BE ABOUT FOOTBALL.
DAMIAN, WHAT'S YOUR FIRST
DECLARATION OF THE DAY?
>> KIRK COUSINS WILL BE THE
FIRST QUARTERBACK IN THE NFC
NORTH THIS YEAR.
>> WHOA.
>> YES.
I'M GOING OUT THERE ON KIRK
COUSINS AND THE MINNESOTA
VIKINGS.
I LOVE WHAT THE VIKINGS DID IN
THE DRAFT.
ADDING A COUPLE PIECES UP FRONT
IN THE OFFENSIVE LINE.
THEY HAVE ARGUABLY THE BEST WIDE
RECEIVER TANDEM.
THEY DRAFTED IRV SMITH.
TIGHT END FROM ALABAMA TO GO
ALONG WITH KYLE RUDOLPH.
EVERYTHING RIGHT NOW IS READY
MADE.
MIKE T. IS TRYING TO JUMP IN ON
THIS.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET HIM.
I AM ADAMANT RIGHT NOW THAT KIRK
COUSINS IS GOING TO GET IT DONE
IN THE NFC NORTH THIS YEAR.
DON'T MAKE ME LOOK LIKE A FOOL,
KIRK COUSINS.
>> THE NFL CONSTITUTIONAL
CRISIS.
I GOT TWO WORDS.
AARON RODGERS.
>> I UNDERSTAND AARON RODGERS
AND NFC NORTH.
I GOT MUCH LOVE AND RESPECT FOR
AARON RODGERS.
BUT I ALSO LOOK AT THIS.
WHAT DID THE GREEN BAY PACKERS,
HOW MUCH ADDITION DID THE
PACKERS ADD TO AARON RODGERS,
THEIR OFFENSE TO HELP AARON
RODGERS THIS UPCOMING YEAR?
NOT MUCH.
I DIDN'T SEE MUCH OF ANYTHING
THIS YEAR.
>> LIKE I SAID, WITH KIRK
COUSINS, THIS IS THE YEAR IN
GETTING PAID A BOATLOAD OF
MONEY.
THE MINNESOTA VIKINGS DRAFTED
GUYS UP FRONT TO HELP THE
OFFENSIVE LINE.
I THINK THIS IS THE YEAR THAT
KIRK COUSINS MAKES A STATEMENT
IN THE NATIONAL FOOTBALL LEAGUE.
>> IF HE DOES, WHAT DOES THAT
MEAN FOR THE VIKINGS?
HOW FAR CAN THEY TAKE IT?
>> THEY CAN GO TO THE SUPER
BOWL.
>> OH, BOY.
>> IF YOU HAVE --
>> IF THAT'S HOW WE DO
DECLARATIONS --
>> IF YOU HAVEN'T FIGURED IT
OUT, I'M PRETTY BULLISH ON THE
MINNESOTA VIKINGS.
>> DAMIAN, WE KNOW THE SIGN OF A
GREAT PLAYER WHEN THEY MAKE
EVERYBODY AROUND THEM BETTER.
AARON RODGERS, THAT HE COULD
ELEVATE THE PLAY OF HIS
TEAMMATES.
I AGREE MINNESOTA HAS HAD A GOOD
OFF-SEASON.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, ISN'T
AARON RODGERS THE BETTER PLAYER
THAN KIRK COUSINS.
>> COUSINS HAS THE HIGHEST
COMPLETION PERCENTAGE THAN ANY
NFC NORTH QUARTERBACK.
HE WAS ONLY 1-6-1 AGAINST TEAMS
WITH WINNING RECORDS.
OBVIOUSLY, GOT TO DO BETTER THAN
THAT.
MIKE TANNENBAUM, WHAT IS YOUR
DECLARATION.
>> KYLE MURRAY WILL NOT PLAY
IN -- HIS PLAY STYLE IS SIMILAR
TO MARCUS MARIOTA.
MARCUS MARIOTA, THROUGHOUT HIS
CAREER, NEVER PLAYED IN 16
GAMES.
WHILE KYLER MURRAY IS A DYNAMIC
ATHLETE BECAUSE OF HIS BUILD, I
THINK AT SOME POINT IT'S GOING
TO BE HARD FOR HIM TO ANSWER THE
BELL AT SOME SUNDAY THIS SEASON
AND I CAN SEE HIM MISSING AT
LEAST ONE GAME.
MY DECLARATION IS KYLER MURRAY,
BASED ON HIS SIZE, BASED ON THE
WAY HE PLAYS, HE WILL NOT PLAY
IN 16 GAMES.
>> A LOT OF EXCITEMENT ABOUT
KYLER MURRAY.
IN ARIZONA THE FIRST YEAR.
HE IS A SCRAMBLER.
HE SCRAMBLED 41 TIMES, NINTH
MOST OF ANY FBS QUARTERBACK.
THAT'S GOING TO BE PART OF HIS
GAME.
THEY SAY THAT THAT HELPS WHEN
THERE ARE QUESTIONS ON THE
OFFENSIVE LINE.
DO YOU BUY IT OR DO THEY NEED TO
BE BETTER UP FRONT?
>> NO, THEY NEED TO BE BETTER UP
FRONT.
>> I'M A BIG BELIEVER, FOOTBALL
ISN'T COMPLICATED.
YOU GOT TO BLOCK, YOU GOT TO
TACKLE, CATCH AND ALL THOSE
TYPES OF THINGS.
WHAT WE SAW FROM THE ARIZONA
CARDINALS LAST YEAR, THEY
COULDN'T BLOCK THEIR WAY OUT OF
A WET PAPER BAG.
THIS IS GOING TO BE -- THIS IS
GOING TO BE A SITUATION THAT
BEARS WATCHING AS FAR AS KYLER
MURRAY AND PROTECTING MOVING
FORWARD.
>> BY THE WAY, WE HEARD THE SAME
SPIEL WHEN I WAS TRYING TO SIGN
DAMIAN WOODY.
HE REMINDED US HOW IMPORTANT THE
OFFENSIVE LINE IS.
>> YEAH.
LISTEN, THE TAPE DON'T LIE.
TAPE DOESN'T LIE.
>> I LIKE TO TAKE CARE OF
DAMIAN.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> WE GOT MORE DO, THOUGH.
COMING UP ON "NFL LIVE," AS WE
MENTIONED EARLIER, INDEPENDENCE
DAY IS TOMORROW.
WE'RE NOT ON THE AIR TOMORROW.
WE'RE GOING TO CELEBRATE A DAY
EARLY WITH THE NFL'S MOST
INDEPENDENT PLAYS.
LOOKING AT THE GUYS WHO CAN DO
IT ALL BY THEMSELVES.
SPEAKING OF DOING IT ALL, CAM
NEWTON MAY BE REHABBING HIS
THROWING ARM, BUT THAT DOESN'T
MEAN HE CAN'T CATCH.
WHICH QUARTERBACK HAS THE BEST
HANDS?
DAMIAN WOODY IS GOING TO TAKE A
SHOT AT RANKING THOSE.
JALEN RAMSEY, HAS HE CHANGED HIS
WAYS?
WE'LL BRING HIM IN LIVE.
HE'LL TELL US.
>> I GO OUT THERE WITH A LITTLE
FLAG.
SOMETIMES I GO OUT THERE AND LET
THE RECEIVER KNOW THIS IS GOING
TO BE A LONG GAME, YOU'RE TRASH
COMPARED TO ME.
I got a very, very small loan
from my father.
You gotta start somewhere.
I'm a reporter for
The New York Times.
The when, the where
bank statements, tax returns,
it's out, dozens of copy records
of deeds and reports.
1995 showed that he was
bleeding money.
Go through it all,
understand it all
Holy sh**
Number by number,
brick by brick.
That's when we realized.
That's fraud.
I built this empire and
I did it by myself.
New for summer,
it's Bud Light Lemon Tea.
That's fraud.
Brewed with REAL lemon peels
and aged on REAL tea leaves.
Yes, it's real.
No, you're not dreaming.
Hey, don't do that.
♪  ♪
Pieces or Cups?
Pieces in Cups!
Man, we're killing
it over here, huh?
Not sorry. Reese's.
In every trip,
there's room for more
than just the business
ityou came for.uh?
♪♪
Whether that's taking in
every moment,
or capturing a moment
worth bringing back.
That's room for possibility.
♪♪
[sprinklers]
[label tearing]
[bottle opens]
Yay!
[aahhh]
[label tearing]
[bottle opens]
[aahhh]
[label tearing]
[bottle opens]
[aahhh]
I switched to MiraLAX
for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives
forcefully stimulate
the nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX works with
the water in your
body to unblock your
system naturally.
And it doesn't cause
bloating,
cramping, gas,
or sudden urgency.
MiraLAX.
Look for the pink cap.
So I can buy from
Enterprise Car Sales and you'll
take ANY trade-in?
That's right!
Great!
Here you go...
Well, it does need
to be a vehicle.
But - I need this out of
my house.
(VO) With fair, transparent
value for every trade-in...
Enterprise makes it easy.
>> Announcer: "NFL LIVE" IS
BROUGHT TO YOU BY PIZZA HUT.
NO ONE OUT-PIZZAS THE HUT.
>>> IT'S SOMETHING THAT MY MOM
WARNS ME ABOUT.
YOU ONLY GET ONE SET OF TEETH.
>> FROM EAR TO EAR, HE'S ALWAYS
SMILING.
>> HE'S ALWAYS KIDDING AROUND
AND KEEPING IT LIGHT.
IF I'M FEELING GOOD, I KNOW THAT
IT'S GOING TO BE CONTAGIOUS
ENOUGH AROUND OTHERS.
>> CAM NEWTON IS SMILING BECAUSE
HE'S AWESOME.
HE CAN RUN AND THROW AND
APPARENTLY HE CAN CATCH.
RECENTLY SHOWING UP, ONE HAND
BEHIND HIS BACK.
ODELL BECKHAM HAS NOTHING ON
CAM.
SO I KNOW DAMIAN ALWAYS SAYS WE
DON'T GIVE QUARTERBACKS ENOUGH
ATTENTION AROUND HERE.
>> QUARTERBACK CATCHES OF
ALL-TIME.
THIS MOHAMED SANU CATCH.
LOOK AT THE REST OF THE WAY, TO
THE END ZONE.
THE SWEET DIVE TO THE PYLON.
MOST PLACES.
>> ANDREW LUCK IN COLLEGE.
HE HAD A COUPLE TARGETS LAST
SEASON.
LOOK AT THIS ONE-HANDED CATCH HE
MADE AT STANFORD.
LOOK AT THAT FOOT INBOUNDS.
NOT A CATCH IN THE NFL.
>> NOT A CATCH IN THE NFL.
>> GOT TO DRAG IT.
THESE ARE GREAT ATHLETES.
>> THAT'S PRETTY CLEAR THERE.
BUT I DON'T THINK THEY'RE GOING
TO HAVE TOO MUCH OF THAT.
>> HOW COULD WE FORGET.
>> QUARTERBACK, SUPER BOWL
HISTORY, NICK FOLES IS ACTING
JOB MIECHB MORE IMPRESSIVE THAN
THE CATCH ITSELF.
WHAT A MOMENT.
ALL-TIME MOMENT IN NFL AROUND
CERTAINLY EAGLES HISTORY.
OBVIOUSLY QUARTERBACKS ARE
ALL-AROUND ATHLETES TOO IN SOME
CASES.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
IT HURT YOU.
>> IT HURTS TO GIVE THIS MUCH
PRAISE TO QUARTERBACKS.
HERE WE ARE.
JULY 3rd.
WE'RE GOING TO DO IT.
WE'RE GOING TO GRIND OUT THIS
CONTENT.
DAMIAN, I WANT YOUR LIST OF THE
MOST VERSATILE QUARTERBACKS
CURRENTLY PLAYING IN THE NFL.
>> NUMBER 5, WE'RE GOING TO
START WITH THIS BIG GUY RIGHT
HERE.
JOSH ALLEN.
THE THING I LIKE -- TALKING
ABOUT HIS CANNON ARM.
I DIDN'T KNOW HE WAS AN OLYMPIC
HURDLER AS WELL.
JUMPING OVER THE MINNESOTA
VIKING DEFENDER THERE.
THAT WAS A HUGE PLAY IN THAT
BUFFALO BILLS WIN UP IN
MINNESOTA LAST YEAR.
SO THIS DUDE IS A TREMENDOUS
ATHLETE.
LOOK FOR HIM TO HAVE A BIG YEAR
THIS YEAR.
>> HE LED THE BILLS RUSHING.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> EVERYTHING THAT DAMIAN SAID,
HE'S BIG, STRONG, CAN MAKE ALL
THE THROWS.
HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO LEARN HOW
TO CORRAL THAT IN SO HE CAN PLAY
A FULL SEASON.
HE'S GOING TO TAKE A LOT OF
HITS.
>> YOU MEAN PLAY QUARTERBACK.
>> NUMBER 4 RIGHT HERE.
WE'RE GOING TO GO WITH MITCHELL
TRUBISKY.
I ALWAYS WANT TO CALL MITCHELL
VICK.
HE LOOKS LIKE -- GOES ALL THE
WAY BACK TO THE -- THIS PLAY
HERE AGAINST THE NEW ENGLAND
PATRIOTS, YOU WATCH THIS GUY
RUN, HE'S A REALLY GOOD ATHLETE,
HE CAN RUN WITH THE FOOTBALL IN
HIS HANDS.
DANGEROUS IN RUNNING THE
FOOTBALL AGAIN.
HE TAKES OFF IN THE POCKET.
HE'S PULLING AWAY FROM PEOPLE
HERE.
SO LISTEN THE DEFENSE GOT TO
DEFEND BOTH OF THE ASPECTS OF
THE QUARTERBACK, MAKES IT
AWFULLY HUFF.
>> THE OFFENSIVE PLAY TO HIS
STRENGTH.
A LOT THE ANDY REID CONCEPT.
THAT'S A HARD OFFENSE TO DEFEND.
NUMBER 3.
>> NUMBER 3.
>> I CAN DO BOTH.
GOT BIG BEN HERE.
WE ALL KNOW BIG BEN IS A FUTURE
HALL OF FAMER.
HOW MUCH THIS, PLAYING
SITUATIONAL FOOTBALL.
WE TALK ABOUT SITUATIONAL
FOOTBALL DOWNED THE BALL INSIDE
THE 1 YARD LINE.
HUGE PLAY AGAIN.
BIG BEN SHOWING OFF WITH ANOTHER
BOOT PUNT.
SETTING IT UP RIGHT HERE.
SETTING UP WITH THE SPECIAL
TEAMS.
NOT ONLY GO OUT THERE -- SET
YOUR FIELD POSITION UP.
>> GET PAID.
>> HE MUST ENJOY THAT.
>> HE MUST BE LOVING IT.
>> SO NUMBER TWO, WE GOT KILLER
CAM.
CAM NEWTON RIGHT HERE.
LISTEN, CAM NEWTON IS A FREAK OF
NATURE.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE RIGHT HERE,
LITTLE TRICK.
BOOM.
DROP THE HAMMER DOWN ON THE
DEFENSIVE LINEMAN.
HOW MANY QUARTERBACKS ARE
WILLING TO THROW THEIR SHOULDER
IN ON A DEFENSIVE LINEMAN AND
KNOCK HIM DOWN TO THE GROUND.
CAM IS A BIG BOY.
SO IT REALLY DOESN'T SURPRISE ME
THAT HE'S KNOCKED THAT DEFENSIVE
LINEMAN ON HIS BUTT.
AGAIN, OFFENSIVE LINEMAN CAN
APPRECIATE A QUARTERBACK.
ONE THAT'S BODYING FOR THE PLAY.
>> HE'S PHYSICALLY IMPOSING.
WHEN YOU SEE HIM COME OUT FROM
WARMUPS, HE'S A PHYSICALLY
IMPOSING PLAYER THAT HAPPENS TO
BE A QUARTERBACK.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
>> QUARTERBACK SEGMENT WITHOUT
YOU TALKING ABOUT BLOCKING.
UNBELIEVABLE.
>> GOT TO HAVE --
>> THIS GUY.
>> THIS RIGHT HERE, HALL OF
FAMER RIGHT HERE, PATRICK
MAHOMES.
WE TALK ABOUT HIM AS A -- AS A
FATHER, YOU TALK ABOUT HAVING
YOUR KIDS INVOLVED IN MORE THAN
ONE SPORT.
HERE'S WHY.
YOU TAKE A GUY IN PATRICK
MAHOMES, GREAT FOOTBALL PLAYER,
ALSO A GREAT BASEBALL PLAYER.
YOU SEE HIM THROWING FROM ALL
DIFFERENT ARM ANGLES, BEING ABLE
TO MAKE PLAYS.
THROWING WITH HIS LEFT HAND.
HE DID THIS TIME AFTER TIME
AGAIN DURING THE SEASON.
THAT MADE HIM SPECIAL.
NO-LOOK PASSES.
TO ME, THAT'S A PART OF A PLAN.
MULTIPLE SPORTS, THEY KIND OF
INTERTWINE WITH EACH OTHER.
THERE'S A BIG REASON WHY HE WAS
NFL MVP LAST YEAR.
>> MIKE, WHEN YOU'RE EVALUATING
QUARTERBACKS, HOW MUCH DOES IT
FACTOR IN HOW ATHLETIC THEY ARE
AND THEY CAN DO THIS STUFF?
>> BEING ABLE TO BUY A SECOND
CHANCE, WE TALKED ABOUT KYLER
MURRAY BEHIND THE OFFENSIVE
LINE, THE FACT THAT HE'LL BE
ABLE TO AVOID, MOVE UP IN THE
POCKET, SOMETIMES IT'S NOT ABOUT
YARDS, BUT AVOIDING THE BIG HIT,
EXTENDING THE PLAY.
KEEPING YOUR EYES DOWN THE
FIELD.
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT.
IT'S A SKILL THAT TRANSFERS FROM
COLLEGE TO PROS.
>> YOU GUYS -- TRIVIA TIME.
DO YOU KNOW WHICH ACTIVE NFL
QUARTERBACK HAS THE MOST CAREER
CATCHES?
>> THEY DON'T KNOW.
>> NO.
>> DREW BREES.
HE HAS EIGHT.
>> WOW.
>> HOW ABOUT THAT.
>> REALLY?
>> WE'LL RUN THEM BACK.
>> WE'LL HAVE TO SEE THAT.
LATER IN THE SUMMER, WE'LL DO
DREW BREES HIGHLIGHTS.
>> WE NEED THE CONTENT.
>> JALEN RAMSEY HAS NOT BEEN SHY
ABOUT SHARING HIS OPINION ON
THINGS LIKE QUARTERBACK
RANKINGS.
NOW HE'S GOT A SUPER BOWL MVP
LEADING HIS OFFENSE.
DOES JALEN THINK
(Client's Voice)
Remember that degree
you got in taxation?
(Danny)
Of course you don't
because you didn't!
Your job isn't
understanding tax code...
it's understanding why that...
will get him a body like that...
MOVE!
...that.
Your job isn't
doing hard work...
Here.
...it's making
her do hard work...
...and getting paid for it.
(VO)
Snap and sort your expenses to
save over $4,600 at tax time.
(Danny)
Jody...
...it's time to get yours!
(VO)
QUICKBOOKS. BACKING YOU.
The hamsters, run hopelessly in
their cage.
Content on their endless quest,
to nowhere.
But perhaps this year, a more
exhilarating endeavor awaits.
Defy the Laws of human nature,At
the summer of Audi sales event.
Get Exceptional Offers now.
Look! Make a wish!
I wish for a Biggie
Bag from Wendy's.
I wish everyone loved each
other and was always...
That's a great wish, Jimmy.
Get a Bacon Double stack with
a quarter pound of fresh beef,
nuggets, fries and a
drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
>>> IF YOU DREAM ABOUT CATCHING
THIS BALL ON ME, YOU BETTER WAKE
UP AND APOLOGIZE.
I GO OUT WITH A LITTLE SWAG.
>> PUKD OFF BY JALEN RAMSEY.
>> RAMSEY CAME OVER THE TOP.
>> YOU GO OUT THERE AND I LET
THE RECEIVER KNOW EVERY PLAY,
HEY, THIS IS GOING TO BE A LONG
GAME FOR YOU.
I CALL THE OUT THEIR ROUTES TO
LET THEM KNOW.
>> YOU'RE TRASH.
>> PLEASE, WELCOME INTO "NFL
LIVE."
JAGUARS QUARTERBACK JALEN RAMSEY
WHO JOINS US TODAY FROM LONDON,
ENGLAND.
JALEN, I GOT TO START HERE.
I WAS DISMAYED WHEN YOU SAID YOU
WERE GOING TO GET OUT OF THE
BUSINESS OF EVALUATING
QUARTERBACKS.
YOU WERE SO GOOD AT IT.
WHY HAVE YOU DECIDED TO STOP?
>> REALLY, I WENT THROUGH MOST
OF THEM LAST YEAR.
TO BE HONEST, I DIDN'T THINK I
NEEDED TO DO IT AGAIN.
MY OPINIONS DIDN'T SAY TOO MUCH.
SO YEAH.
I JUST DIDN'T FEEL THE NEED TO
DO IT AGAIN.
I WANTED TO PUMP UP NICK A
LITTLE BIT.
I WAS EXCITED TO SEE NICK OUT
THERE.
I WANTED TO PUMP NICK UP A
LITTLE BIT.
YEAH, GOT AWAY FROM IT FOR A
I'LL STILL TALK MY TRASH,
THOUGH.
>> AS YOU WENT AROUND THE
LEAGUE, DID YOU HEAR A LOT ABOUT
THAT INTERVIEW YOU GAVE WHERE
YOU TALKED ABOUT ALL THE
QUARTERBACKS, PEOPLE GIVE YOU A
HARD TIME OR TELL YOU YOU WERE
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, IT WAS OPINION-BASED.
YOU KNOW, WE WERE EXACTLY HOW IT
WENT.
WE WERE TALKING A LITTLE BIT.
WE STARTED OFF NAMING LIKE WHO
WERE THE TOP FIVE QUARTERBACKS
AND GOING DOWN THE LIST.
I WAS KIND OF STILL KEEPING THE
TIME FRAME, HE'S NOT TOP FIVE.
HE'S OVERRATED.
HE'S GOOD, WHATEVER.
WHATEVER I WAS SAYING ABOUT EACH
AND EVERY QUARTERBACK, YEAH,
GIVING SOME OPINIONS.
SOME PEOPLE, OF COURSE, YOU
KNOW, THEY'RE GOING TO AGREE AND
SOME PEOPLE ARE NOT GOING TO
AGREE.
EVERYBODY IS ENTITLED TO THEIR
OWN OPINION.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
YOU MENTIONED YOUR NEW
QUARTERBACK, NICK FOLES JOINING
THE JAGUARS AS A FREE AGENT THIS
YEAR.
WHAT'S THE ONE THING ABOUT HIM
THAT JUMPS OUT AT YOU THAT YOU
MAY NOT HAVE KNOWN BEFORE HE WAS
YOUR TEAMMATE?
>> I MEAN, HE'S JUST -- HOW WELL
HE PRACTICES, I GUESS.
I OF COURSE, NEVER PRACTICED
WITH HIM.
AT MINI-CAMP I SAW HOW HE COMES
OUT AND WORKS HARD AND PUSHES
THE GUYS AND LEADS THE OFFENSE.
IT WAS TRULY IMPRESSIVE.
I HAD KNOWN AND HEARD ABOUT HOW
GOOD OF A TEAMMATE HE WAS AND
HOW GOOD OF A PERSON HE WAS IN
GENERAL.
BUT JUST SEEING HIM IN THE
LOCKER ROOM, BEING IN HIS
PRESENCE AND COMMUNICATING WITH
HIM AND OUR FEW INTERACTIONS, IT
WAS SUPER NICE.
>> STARTING QUARTERBACK IS
OBVIOUSLY A MAJOR CHANGE ON ANY
NFL TEAM.
WHAT'S THE BIGGEST DIFFERENCE IN
THE JAGUARS THIS YEAR VERSUS
LAST YEAR HAVING MADE THAT
CHANGE?
>> I FEEL LIKE IT'S UPGRADE.
OF COURSE, I WAS SAYING -- BLAKE
WAS A REALLY GOOD TEAMMATE TO
EVERYBODY.
HAVING NICK AND A FORMER SUPER
BOWL CHAMPION AND SUPER BOWL
MVP, WE HAVE SUPREME CONFIDENCE
IN HIM AND WE THINK THAT HE'S
GOING TO DO A GOOD JOB OF
LEADING OUR OFFENSE.
OF COURSE ON THE DEFENSIVE SIDE
OF THE BALL, WE ARE OVERFLOWING
WITH CONFIDENCE OVER THERE AND
SAYING WHO WE THINK CAN GET THE
JOB DONE OVER THERE ON THAT
SIDE.
NOW WE GOT SOMEBODY ELSE TO ROLL
WITH THE OTHER GUYS OVER THERE.
WE'RE SUPER EXCITED.
>> THE DEFENSE OBVIOUSLY
COMPLETELY DOMINANT TWO SEASONS
AGO.
YOU KWAME AGONIZINGLY CLOSE TO
THE SUPER BOWL AND LAST YEAR,
DISAPPOINTMENT FOR THE TEAM ALL
THE WAY AROUND.
WHAT GIVES YOU THE CONFIDENCE
THAT THIS CAN BE CLOSER TO 2017
THAN 2018?
>> WE'RE GOING TO BREAK THE
JOURNEY TO BE HONEST.
YOU KNOW, JOURNEY PEOPLE SAY
TRUST THE PROCESS AND STUFF LIKE
THAT.
I REALLY DON'T EVEN BELIEVE IN
WE CAN MAKE HOWEVER MANY PLANS
WE WANT TO IN OUR HEADS AND
WHATEVER WE FEEL THE PROCESS IS.
IT'S TRULY GOING TO BE A
JOURNEY.
IT'S GOING TO BE UPS AND DOWNS,
HIGHS AND LOWS.
WE HAVE TO ROLL WITH ALL OF
THEM.
WE HAVE TO ROLL WITH THE HIGHS
AND THE LOWS.
WE HAVE TO PUSH THROUGH AND MAKE
SURE THAT WE ARE IN POSITION TO
WIN THE DIVISION, WIN THE
CONFERENCE AND GO TO THE SUPER
BOWL AND COMPETE FOR THE SUPER
BOWL.
>> YOU'VE QUICKLY ESTABLISHED
YOURSELF AS ONE OF THE BETTER
PLAYERS AT YOUR POSITION IN THE
LEAGUE.
BUT THE NFL BEING WHAT IT IS,
YOU'RE STILL A WAYS AWAY FROM
FREE AGENCY.
THE JAGUARS PICKED UP YOUR
CONTRACT OPTION FOR 2020.
ANY EXTENSION TALKS YET OR IS
THAT STILL ON THE BACK BURNER?
>> IT'S ON THE BACK BURNER RIGHT
NOW.
BUT THAT'S COMPLETELY FINE.
FIRST ROUND CONTRACTS OUR
STRUCTURE RIGHT NOW.
THE TEAMS HAVE A LOT OF
LEVERAGE.
THEY CAN PICK UP THE FIFTH-YEAR
OPTION.
YOU KNOW, UNLIKE OTHER GUYS WHO
OUT-PLAY THEIR ROOKIE CONTRACT
AND CAN REUP RIGHT NOW AND GET
BASICALLY WHAT THEY'RE WORTH,
FIRST ROUNDERS DON'T HAVE THAT
LUXURY.
WE HAVE THE FIFTH YEAR OPTION
AND AFTER THAT THEY CAN
FRANCHISE TAG AND DO EVERY THING
THEY WANT TO DO.
THEY HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF
LEVERAGE.
I'M GOING TO LET MY AGENT HANDLE
A LOT OF THAT.
I'M GOING TO FOCUS ON WHAT I CAN
FOCUS ON AND PLAY BALL.
HELP THE TEAM WIN WHILE I'M HERE
IN JACKSONVILLE.
HOPEFULLY, I'M HERE FOR A LONG
TIME.
IT'S TIME TO OPEN UP CONTRACT
NEGOTIATIONS.
WE'LL SEE HOW THINGS GO.
OF COURSE, WE WANTED TO GET IT
DONE THIS YEAR.
BUT IT WON'T GET DONE THIS YEAR.
HEY, IT IS WHAT IT IS.
WE TALKED WITH THE JAGUARS AND
EVERYBODY WHO IS IN CHARGE OF
THAT.
THEY KNOW WHAT'S UP.
THEY KNOW --
>> YOU'RE COMING TO US FROM
LONDON TODAY.
A BIG STORY IN THE STATES IS THE
U.S. WOMEN'S SOCCER TEAM BEATING
ENGLAND IN THE WORLD CUP
YESTERDAY.
WHAT'S CAUGHT THE ATTENTION OF A
LOT OF PEOPLE IS ALEX MORGAN --
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS ON IT AS
A KNOWN TRASH TALKER?
>> I LOVED IT, OF COURSE.
LIKE YOU SAID, I'VE BEEN KNOWN
TO TRASH TALK MYSELF AND DO EYE
A LITTLE BIT OF THAT.
I LOVED IT.
I THOUGHT IT WAS VERY FITTING,
OF COURSE.
BECAUSE OF WHO THEY PLAYED,
OBVIOUSLY.
I MEAN, SERVING IT UP, WHY NOT?
HAVE SOME FUN.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE PROFESSIONAL
ATHLETES, OF COURSE, BUT WE'RE
ALSO ENTERTAINERS IN A SENSE.
WE WANT TO KEEP EVERYTHING
INTERESTING.
SO NOW, SHE GAVE PEOPLE
EVERYTHING TO TALK ABOUT, A LOT
TO TALK ABOUT.
I THINK IT'S COOL.
I THINK IT'S GOOD.
>> JALEN RAMSEY, THANK YOU SO
MUCH FOR JOINING US ON "NFL
LIVE" AND SHARING YOUR INSIGHTS.
BEST OF LUCK TO YOU IN COMING
SEASON.
>> APPRECIATE IT.
THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>>> ALL RIGHT.
BACK TO OUR DECLARATIONS.
IF YOU WEREN'T HERE EARLIER,
TOMORROW IS THE FOURTH OF JULY
AND THE DECLARATION OF
INDEPENDENCE.
NFL DECLARATIONS HERE ON "NFL
LIVE."
DAMIAN MADE A DECLARATION
EARLIER ABOUT KIRK COUSINS.
HE WAS VERY VOCIFEROUS.
MIKE, YOU GOT ONE ON THE
JAGUARS?
>> I ABSOLUTELY DO.
I DECLARE THAT NICK FOLES WILL
LEAD THE JACKSONVILLE JAGUARS TO
THE SUPER BOWL REPRESENTING THE
AFC.
I KNOW THAT YOU KNOW THIS
BECAUSE YOU'RE A STUDENT OF THE
GAME.
LAST YEAR THE JAGUARS AVERAGED
LESS THAN 10 POINTS A GAME AND
YOU TAKE WHAT IS ALREADY A
CHAMPIONSHIP LEVEL DEFENSE LED
BY JALEN RAMSEY AND THIS YEAR'S
FIRST ROUND PICK, JOSH ALLEN,
WITH A QUARTERBACK WHO TWO YEARS
AGO, BUT FOR A DROP IN THE NFC
PLAYOFFS, BROUGHT THE EAGLES TO
TWO CONSECUTIVE SUPER BOWLS.
THAT'S MY DECLARATION.
>> THIS IS INTERESTING.
JALEN RAMSEY HAS, IN FACT,
STAYED ON THE LINE AND HEARD
YOUR DK DECLARATION, MIKE
TANNENBAUM.
>> WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS ON
THAT?
>> I LOVE THAT DECLARATION RIGHT
THERE.
SPEAKING OF -- I LOVE IT.
I'M SUPER EXCITED TO HAVE NICK
ON THE TEAM.
WE'RE GOING TO PUT ALL THAT
CONFIDENCE BEHIND HIM AND LET
HIM LEAD THE OFFENSE.
LIKE YOU SAID, THIS DEFENSE WE
HAVE, WE THINK SOME BIG THINGS
COULD BE IN STORE FOR THE 2019
SEASON.
>> JALEN WHEN EVERYBODY IS ON
THE BANDWAGON, REMEMBER WE HAD
THIS CONVERSATION ON JULY 3rd.
THAT WAS MY DECLARATION.
I'M WITH YOU GUYS.
THE BANDWAGON STARTS TODAY.
LET NOT LET ANYBODY ELSE ON.
>> I APPRECIATE YOU STICKING
AROUND.
>> LOVE IT.
>> DECLARATION -- WE SHOULD HAVE
JALEN IN AND DO THE --
>> YOU JUST GO ALL IN.
GO ALL IN ON MY HEAD ABOUT KIRK
COUSINS.
YOU'RE ALL IN ON JACKSONVILLE.
LISTEN, NICK FOLES WAS GREAT
WITH DOUG PEDERSON.
I FELT THEY HAD A CHEMISTRY.
YOU THINK THEY CAN CREATE THAT
IN JACKSONVILLE WITH THIS
DIFFERENT CAST OF CHARACTERS?
>> NO DOUBT ABOUT IT.
IT STARTS WITH THE OFFENSIVE
LINE.
THEY HAVE A VERY GOOD OFFENSIVE
DOUG MARRONE WAS AN OFFENSIVE
LINEMAN, PLAYED, COACHED IT.
NOW HE'S THEIR HEAD COACH.
IT ALLOWS THEM TO TRAVEL, PLAY
WELL ON THE ROAD AND WITH THAT
DEFENSE, THEY'RE LOADED UP
FRONT.
THEY HAVE A LOT OF DEPTH AT PASS
RUSHER WHEN YOU LOOK AT LAST
YEAR'S FIRST ROUND PICK.
NOKE WAY.
AT DEFENSIVE END AND CALAIS
CAMPBELL AND JOSH ALLEN THIS
YEAR.
THEY HAVE DEPTH UP FRONT AND TWO
CORNERS IN RAMSEY.
BLAKE BORTLES.
WE'RE BEING GENEROUS WITH THAT.
NICK FOLES WAS A GOOD
QUARTERBACK.
THAT'S MY DECLARATION.
>> ONE DIFFERENCE, MIGHT BE THE
REASON THEY SIGN THEM, 23
INTERCEPTIONS IN 40 GAMES IN
PHILADELPHIA.
BORTLES HAD 58 INTERCEPTIONS IN
60 GAMES.
THEY SHOULD BE BETTER THERE.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE MORE
DECLARATIONS LATER IN THE SHOW.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK TO SOCCER.
ALEX MORGAN SHOOK UP THE TWITTER
VERSE WITH HER TEA SIPPING --
WHAT COMPARES TO THIS
SURPRISINGLY CONTROVERSIAL ONE.
STAY TUNED TO "NFL LIVE."
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT.
(VO)
Why use Post-it Extreme Notes?
Because they make your message
stick,
getting it said, and done right,
the first time.
(Man off screen)
Aw, C'mon!
(VO)
Stop the Re-work with Post-it
Extreme Notes.
Hiyeeeeeee!
Oh!
We all just got new
smartphones at Cricket!
Hiyeeeeeee!
!Holaaaaa!
OK, biyeeeeee!
Is Bud Light Orange coming
back this summer?
Biyeeeee!!
And never leaving?
And brewed with real
orange peels?
The answer is yes...
...yes...
and yes.
♪
In every trip,
there's room for more
p,          and yes.
than just the business
theryou came for.more
♪♪
Whether that's keeping up
with what you always do...
or training
for something
you've never done before.
That's room
for possibility.
you've never done before.
That's room
for possibility.
♪♪
>>> WITH THE FIRST PICK, THE NEW
ORLEANS PELICANS SELECT DIE ON
WILLIAMSON.
THE KNICKS SELECT R.J. BARRY.
>> I LOVE --
>> MY DREAM CAME TRUE.
>> NBA SUMMER LEAGUE ACTION
FRIDAY.
WE'VE GOT A TRIPLE HEADER
STARTING AT 7:30 EASTERN.
YOU WON'T WANT TO MISS THE
SPECIAL MATCHUP AT 9:30 EASTERN
TIME FEATURING WILLIAMSON AND
BARRETT FACING OFF FOR THE FIRST
TIME AS PROS.
SPEAKING OF THE NBA, LAKERS FAN
DAMIAN WOODY INSISTS THAT WE
TALK ABOUT THE KAWHI LEONARD
FREE AGENCY SITUATION.
STILL WAITING FOR WORD ON WHERE
HE'LL END UP.
IF IT IS THE LAKERS, DAMIAN IS
EXCITED TO SEE THAT PICTURE
THERE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> AN IMPOSING BIG THREE WITH
LeBRON JAMES AND ANTHONY DAVIS.
SO SAY THIS ABOUT 20 TIMES
TODAY, THAT GOT US THINKING
ABOUT NFL BIG THREES AND WE'RE
LOOKING AT SOME PRETTY GOOD ONES
RIGHT HERE.
MIKE TANNENBAUM, WHY DON'T YOU
RANK THEM FOR US.
NUMBER 5 TO 1.
>> NUMBER 5, THE L.A. RAMS.
STAYING IN L.A.
COME ON OVER.
THERE YOU GO.
>> THERE WE GO.
>> THE REASON THEY'RE ONLY FIVE.
I LIKE COOKS, I DON'T SEE HIM AS
AN ELITE RECEIVER, HE'S STRAIGHT
LINE AND FAST.
NOT GREAT CHANGE OF DIRECTION.
THAT'S WHY THEY'RE FIVE FOR ME.
>> GOT THEM TO THE SUPER BOWL.
>> NUMBER 4, THE ATLANTA
FALCONS.
YOU LOOK AT MATT RYAN, SUPER
BOWL QUARTERBACK, JULIO JONES,
ARGUABLY THE BEST RECEIVER IN
THE NFL AND THEN OBVIOUSLY
FREEMAN OFF THE INJURY.
HE'S A GOOD RUNNING BACK.
I THINK THAT'S A REALLY SOLID
THREE GUYS RIGHT THERE.
>> RUNNING BACKS COMING OFF
INJURIES.
THEY CAN REST ON THOSE TOO TWO
GUYS.
>> DRAFTED A COUPLE LINEMEN UP
FRONT.
THAT SHOULD BE GOOD NEWS FOR
MATT RYAN AND DeVONTE FREEMAN.
>> BIG THREE OFFENSIVE LINE.
>>> NUMBER 3, THE DALLAS
COWBOYS.
A LOT OF PEOPLE DON'T REALIZE
THIS.
DAK PRESCOTT, 32-16 AS A
STARTING.
ZEKE ELLIOTT A RUNNING BACK AS
THERE IS IN THE LEAGUE, AMARI
COOPER, ALL THEY DID WAS GO 7-2
AFTER THE TRADE AND THEY WERE
NUMBER ONE OVER THE LAST NINE
GAMES ON THIRD DOWN.
>> NUMBER 2, WHAT DO YOU GOT?
>> THE NEW ORLEANS SAINTS LED BY
FUTURE HALL OF FAMER DREW BREES
AT QUARTERBACK.
MICHAEL THOMAS WHO IS NOT BAD.
JULIO JONES NOT FAR BEHIND.
WHAT I LOVE ABOUT HIM, HE'S A
GREAT RUNNING BACK AND OUT OF
THE BACKFIELD.
>> WHO COULD BE BETTER THAN
THAT?
>> LET'S -- ONE OF YOUR FORMER
TEAMS.
THE NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS,
SOMEONE WHO HAS BEEN TO THE --
TOM BRADY, BEST QUARTERBACK OF
ALL-TIME, JULIAN EDELMAN, I HAVE
SO MUCH RESPECT AND ADMIRATION
FROM HIM.
HE'S WILLED HIMSELF INTO A GREAT
PLAYER.
SONY MICHEL ISN'T A GREAT
PLAYER -- HE WAS A FIRST ROUND
PICK.
GOT BETTER AS THE YEAR WENT ON.
HE'S GOING TO TURN INTO BEING A
GOOD NFL RUNNING BACK.
TOM BRADY, IT STARTS WITH HIM.
>> YOU KNOW, I AM DISAPPOINTED
IN YOU RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW WHY?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU DON'T
BELIEVE IN KIRK COUSINS.
THIS MIGHT BE THE BEST DUO IN
THE LEAGUE IN ADAM AND STEPHAN
DIGS.
WHAT IS UP WITH THE HATE AGAINST
THE MINNESOTA VIKINGS?
>> YOU NEED TO EXPLAIN TO THE
PURPLE PEOPLE EATERS OUT THERE.
>> I WATCHED THE TAPE, THAT'S I
CAN'T.
>> WHOA.
>> THAT IS A GOOD GROUP.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE -- OBVIOUSLY
KANSAS CITY.
THESE ARE ALL GOOD.
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT HALL OF
FAME QUARTERBACK, TOM BRADY.
HALL OF FAME QUARTERBACK IN DREW
BREES.
MATT RYAN HAS A HALL OF FAME
CREDENTIALS POSSIBLY AND I THINK
THAT'S A REALLY HIGH LEVEL.
NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED OF OVER
HERE.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT IF DALVIN
COOK IS A HEALTHY RUNNING BACK,
HE COULD BE GOOD ENOUGH TO PUT
THEM IN THIS CATEGORY.
>> I THINK DALVIN COOK IS A GAME
CHANGER.
KIRK COUSINS IS A GOOD RUNNING
GAME.
PLAY ACTION.
DALVIN COOK HOPEFULLY NOT ONLY
HELPS THE RUNNING GAME BUT THEIR
PASSING GAME.
>> THOSE ARE THE BIG THREES.
STILL NOTHING ON KAWHI.
WE'LL LET YOU KNOW IF WE SEE
ANYTHING.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK TO TIGHTI
HAD NJOKU ABOUT ALL
♪  ♪
New for summer.
Here for summer.
Arriving...this summer.
It's Bud Light Lemon Tea.
New for summer.
♪♪
I've been waiting my whole life
for this.
♪♪
You ready?
Are you?
♪♪
Woo.
Look! Make a wish!
I wish for a Biggie
Bag from Wendy's.
I wish everyone loved each
other and was always...
That's a great wish, Jimmy.
Get a Bacon Double stack with
a quarter pound of fresh beef,
nuggets, fries and a
drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
>>> BREAKING NEWS INTO "NFNFL
LIVE."
COWBOYS RUNNING BABACK, EZEKIEL
ELLIOTT HAS BEEN INFORMED HE
WILL NOT BE SUSPENDED FOR HIS
ROLE IN THAT RECENT ALTERCATION
IN LAS VEGAS WITH THE SECURITY
GUARD THAT WE DISCUSSED AT THE
TOP OF THE SHOW.
ELLIOTT MET WITH COMMISSIONER
ROGER GOODELL YESTERDAY AND
ISSUED A STATEMENT LAST NIGHT
ABOUT HIS INVOLVEMENT THERE,
APOLOGIZING AND WE ARE NOW BEING
INFORMED THAT HE WILL NOT FACE
ANOTHER SUSPENSION.
SO OBVIOUSLY A RELIEF FOR
EZEKIEL ELLIOTT AND FOR THE
COWBOYS THERE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
LISTEN, AS A VETERAN IN THE
LOCKER ROOM, THIS IS EXACTLY THE
OUTCOME YOU WANTED.
YOU WANT ALL YOUR GUYS, ALL
HANDS ON DECK TO BE AVAILABLE.
THIS IS AN IMPORTANT YEAR FOR
EVERYONE WITHIN THE DALLAS
COWBOYS ORGANIZATION FROM THE
HEAD COACH ON DOWN.
OBVIOUSLY, MAYBE THE MOST
IMPORTANT PLAYER FOR THE TEAM IS
GOING TO BE AVAILABLE AT THE
START OF THE SEASON.
>> ARE YOU SURPRISED, MIKE?
>> I WAS MILDLY SURPRISED.
AGAIN, THE PERSONAL CONDUCT
POLICY'S STANDARD IS LOWER THAN
CRIMINAL CONDUCT.
THE COMMISSIONER COULD HAVE
SUSPENDED HIM BECAUSE HE'S A
REPEAT OFFENDER AND THE FACT
THAT HE BROUGHT HIM TO NEW YORK
CITY SHOWS IT WAS SIGNIFICANT
ENOUGH FOR A FACE-TO-FACE
MEETING.
LOOK, AT THE END OF THE DAY,
HOPEFULLY EZEKIEL ELLIOTT HAS
LEARNED AND ALL THESE SORT OF
BUMPS IN THE ROAD FROM OFF THE
FIELD ARE IN HIS PAST BECAUSE HE
IS A GREAT PLAYER AND BY ALL
ACCOUNTS A GOOD TEAMMATE AS
WELL.
HOPEFULLY HE'S LEARNED FROM THIS
AND MOVED ON.
>> WE TALKED EARLIER IN THE SHOW
ABOUT THE KIND OF CONVERSATION
YOU HAVE WITH A PLAYER IN THIS
SITUATION IF YOU'RE IN THE FRONT
OFFICE.
DOES THE FACT THAT HE ISN'T
BEING SUSPENDED CHANGE ANY PART
OF THAT MESSAGE OR MAKE IT MORE
DIFFICULT TO DELIVER?
>> NO.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE A STERN, DIRECT
AND HARD CONVERSATION THAT YOUR
BEHAVIOR IS NOT ACCEPTABLE AND
EVEN THOUGH IT DIDN'T RISE TO
THE LEVEL OF SUSPENSION, IT'S
STILL NOT CONDUCT BECOMING OF A
DALLAS COWBOY.
AGAIN, IF I WAS IN THE FRONT
OFFICE MAKING THE DECISION, I
WOULD HIT PAUSE ON THE CONTRACT
EXTENSION AND I WOULD PUT MY
EFFORTS AND ENERGY INTO THE GOOD
PLAYERS AND THE PLAYERS THAT
HAVE HANDLED THEMSELVES THE
RIGHT WAY OFF THE FIELD STARTING
WITH THE QUARTERBACK, DAK
PRESCOTT AND THEIR RECEIVER,
AMARI COOPER.
HOPEFULLY, IT'S A LESSON LEARNED
FOR ZEKE ELLIOTT, IT DOESN'T
HAPPEN AGAIN.
IF I'M THE DALLAS COWBOYS, I
HAVE TO HAVE THAT CONVERSATION
WITH HIM AND TELL HIM WHAT WE'RE
THINKING AND WHY WE'RE THINKING
IT.
>> DAMIAN?
>> AGAIN, AS A PLAYER IN THE
LOCKER ROOM, THIS IS WHAT YOU
WANT TO HEAR.
HE'S GOING TO BE AVAILABLE AND
WE CAN GO OUT AND WIN FOOTBALL
GAMES.
>> I MEAN, IS THERE ANYTHING TO
THE IDEA HE'S NOT BEING SPEBDED
SO YOU STILL HAVE TO SORT OF
MAKE SURE SOMETHING IT LEARNED
FROM THIS, RIGHT, AS A PLAYER?
>> THERE'S SOMETHING FOR THE
DALLAS COWBOYS INTERNALLY FOR
THE ORGANIZATION THEY WANT TO
DO.
FOR A VETERAN, DON'T MESS WITH
MY MONEY.
THAT'S MY BIGGEST THING.
WHEN YOU'RE NOT THERE, YOU
AFFECT MY PLAY.
SO STAY ON THE STRAIGHT AND
NARROW SO WE CAN WIN FOOTBALL
GAMES.
>> NOT THIS NECESSARILY HAPPENED
TO YOU, BUT BEING CALLED INTO
THE COMMISSIONER'S OFFICE EVEN
WITH NO SUSPENSION, SHOULD
THAT --
>> IT SHOULD BE.
SCARED STRAIGHT.
YOU GOT TO TALK TO BIG BAD ROGER
GOODELL, MAKE SURE I'M ON THE
STRAIGHT AND NARROW.
HOPEFULLY EZEKIEL HAS LEARNED
FROM THIS AND THE COWBOYS CAN
MOVE FORWARD NOW.
>> THAT'S THE PART THAT THERE'S
A LOT OF PEOPLE IN THE NFL
COMMUNITY THAT ARE SURPRISED.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED TWO YEARS
AGO, THE LAST TIME, GOT
SUSPENDED, HAD TO GO TO THE
LEAGUE OFFICE.
YOU WOULD THINK WITH THE
CONTRACT ON THE HORIZON, HE
WOULD TRY TO BE IMPECCABLE.
HOPEFULLY HE'S LEARNED FROM IT
AND CAN MOVE ON.
>> OBVIOUSLY, THIS CLEARS THE
DECK IN TERMS OF A MAJOR
CONCERN.
THEY HAVE CONTRACT SITUATION
TOSS WORK THROUGH HEADING INTO
CAMP.
YOU SEE THEM PRIEPD FOR A REAL
SERIES RUN?
>> I THINK THE DALLAS COWBOYS
CAN REPRESENT IN THE SUPER BOWL.
THE WAY THAT DAK PRESCOTT PLAYED
AFTER THE TRADE OF AMARI COOPER
FROM OAKLAND, THE NUMBERS SPEAK
FOR THEMSELVES.
ACROSS THE BOARD.
COMPLETION PERCENTAGE, YARDS PER
ATTEMPT.
THIRD DOWN.
ALL THOSE NUMBERS WERE
SIGNIFICANTLY BETTER WITH AMARI
COOPER.
YOU KNOW, DURING THE TRADE,
DURING THE SEASON, SO IMAGINE
NOW IN THE OFF-SEASON, YOU GOT A
NEW OFFENSIVE COORDINATOR IN
KELLEN MOORE.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW THAT'S GOING
TO WORK OUT, BUT YOU WOULD THINK
IT WOULD ACCENTUATE ALL PARTS OF
DAK'S GAME.
THIS OFFENSE, THIS TEAM IN
GENERAL TO ME IS ONE OF THE
BETTER TEAMS IN THE NATIONAL
FOOTBALL LEAGUE.
>> ONLY THREE TEAMS IN THE
LEAGUE WON MORE GAMES THAN THE
COWBOYS THE LAST THREE YEARS.
THE CHIEFS, THE PATRIOTS AND THE
STEELERS.
THAT'S PRETTY GOOD COMPANY.
>> AGAIN, I DON'T THINK DAK
PRESCOTT GETS ENOUGH CREDIT.
HE'S 32-16 AS A STARTER.
THE ULTIMATE MEASURE OF A
QUARTERBACK IS HIS ONE LOSS
RECORD.
YOU GO BACK TO THE LAST YEAR,
PASSER RATING OF 122 ON PLAY
ACTION PLAYS.
IT SHOWS YOU THE IMPORTANCE OF
EZEKIEL ELLIOTT'S AVAILABILITY
AS YOU MENTIONED, DAMIAN.
DEPENDING ON THE HEALTH OF
CARSON WENTZ, DALLAS HAS A
REASONABLE CHANCE OF WINNING
THIS DIVISION.
OVERS LAST COUPLE YEARS,
PHILADELPHIA HAS DONE A GOOD JOB
OF HAVING BEEN BEHIND WENTZ.
FOLES ISN'T THERE.
WENTZ HAS TO OVERKONL THAT
ISSUE.
CAN HE STAY HEALTHY FOR 16
GAMES.
YOU LOOK AT THE WAY DALLAS HAS
BUILT ITS TEAM ON BOTH SIDES OF
THE BALL.
>> THE NFL RELEASED A STATEMENT
ON THIS ISSUE REGARDING EZEKIEL
ELLIOTT.
ANNOUNCING THAT HE WON'T BE
SUSPENDED.
IMMEDIATELY FOLLOWING REPORTS OF
AN INCIDENT IN LAS VEGAS IN MAY,
THE NFL CONDUCT A COMPREHENSIVE
INVESTIGATION THAT INCLUDED
INTERVIEWS WITH MULTIPLE
WITNESSES, INCLUDING SECURITY
PERSONNEL AND OTHERS WITH DIRECT
INVOLVEMENT.
AS WELL AS A REVIEW OF
DOCUMENTARY AND OTHER
INFORMATION.
ON TUESDAY, AS PART OF THE
REVIEW, NFL COMMISSIONER ROGER
GOODELL MET WITH MR. ELLIOTT TO
REINFORCE THE STANDARDS OF
CONDUCT EXPECTED OF HIM AND THE
CONSEQUENCES FOR FAILING TO MEET
THOSE STANDARDS.
MR. ELLIOTT ACKNOWLEDGED HE
DEMONSTRATED POOR JUDGMENT AND
COMMITTED TO MAKE BETTER CHOICES
IN THE FUTURE.
HE VOLUNTEERED TO TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THE RESOURCES AVAILABLE TO
HIM TO HELP HIM TO GROW
PERSONALLY.
COMMISSIONER GOODELL DETERMINED
THERE WAS NO VIOLATION OF THE
PERSONAL CONDUCT POLICY AND NO
FURTHER ACTION IS WARRANTED.
SO STATEMENT CONFIRMING WHAT WE
WERE TOLD.
ANY QUICK REACTIONS THERE?
>> GOT LUCKY.
>> HE GOT LUCKY.
HE COULD HAVE EASILY BEEN
SUSPENDED AGAIN.
MIKE, YOU HAD TOUCHED UPON IT
PRIOR.
USUALLY IN THESE SITUATIONS, YOU
KNOW, THIS IS YOUR SECOND TIME
GOING TO NEW YORK AND TALKING TO
THE COMMISSIONER.
YOU'VE BEEN SUSPENDED BEFORE
ALREADY.
YOU GET OFF WITH NO PUNISHMENT.
HE'S VERY FORTUNATE TO BE IN
THIS SITUATION.
>> THEY TOUCHED ON IT IN A
LETTER THERE THAT LEAGUE AND THE
UNION DESERVE A LOT OF CREDIT,
THE RESOURCES AVAILABLE TO
PLAYERS, TO COACHES, TO STAFF IN
TERMS OF, IF YOU FEEL LIKE YOU
NEED HELP AND THERE ARE A LOT OF
RESOURCES BEHIND THE SCENES.
HOPEFULLY IF HE NEEDS THAT, HE
TAKES ADVANTAGE OF IT AND I KNOW
THEY MENTIONED THAT IN A LETTER.
THAT'S AN IMPORTANT ASPECT OF
THE COLLECTIVE BARGAINING
AGREEMENT.
THEY ARE TRYING TO HELP PLAYERS.
>> ONCE AGAIN, THE NEWS ON
COWBOYS RUNNING BACK, EZEKIEL
ELLIOTT, NO PUNISHMENT, NO
SUSPENSION AS A RESULT OF HIS
MOST RECENT INCIDENT.
>> WHEN WE RETURN, ALEX MORGAN
WOKE UP SOCIAL MEDIA AFTER
CASUALLY SIPPING HER TEA
TUESDAY.
WE'LL SHOW YOU SOME NFL
CELEBRATIONS THAT ALEX REMINDED
US OF.
>> THEY WANT A SHOW.
THEY'RE ABOUT TO GET ONE.
>> GOT YOUR POPCORN READY.
>> GET YOUR POPCORN READY.
>> THAT'S ALL FOLKS.
It's Rukmini here from
The New York Times .
Hey, you see this?
THIS IS A PAYDAY BAR.
AND THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
YOU NEED TO KNOW ABOUT IT.
IT HAS A TRUCK LOAD OF PEANUTS
SURROUNDING SWEET CARAMEL.
I MEAN HOLY...
(DRILL SOUND)
LOOK AT ALL THOSE PEANUTS.
BEST PART IS IT HELPS
YOU GET THROUGH YOUR DAY.
PAYDAY.
BEST PART IS IT HELPS
YOU GET THROUGH YOUR DAY.
You can tell from
the airborne citrus
that Bud Light Lime, Orange
and Lemon Tea
are brewed with real lime,
orange and lemon peels.
Well, maybe you can't,
but there are some
firm context clues.
In every trip,
there's room for more
than just the business
you came for.
♪♪
Whether that's taking in
every moment,
or capturing a moment
worth bringing back.
That's room for possibility.
♪♪
Feed your imagination.
Feed your excitement.
Feed...your hunger.
When heroes get hungry,
they get the $12 Extra Large,
Superhero Pizza
at Papa John's.
they get the $12 Extra Large,
Superhero Pizza
(door bell rings)
It's open!
Hey.
This is amazing.
With moderate to severe
ulcerative colitis,
Are you okay?
even when I was there,
I never knew when my symptoms
would keep us apart.
So I talked to my doctor
about HUMIRA.
I learned HUMIRA can help get,
and keep UC under control
when other medications haven't
worked well enough.
And it helps people achieve
control that lasts.
So you can experience few
or no symptoms.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have
happened;
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions, and
new or worsening heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like symptoms
or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if you have
an infection.
Be there for you, and them.
Ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA,
control is possible.
>> Announcer: KEEP UP WITH YOUR
FAVORITE TEAM ON THE GO WITH THE
NFL APP.
GET ALL YOUR UPDATES, SCORES AND
LIVE GAMES DURING THE SEASON.
DOWNLOAD THE NFL APP FROM YOUR
APP STORE.
>>> THE ESPYS AUCTION IS WHERE
YOU CAN BID ON ONCE IN A
LIFETIME EXPERIENCES LIKE
JOINING ME ON THE SET OF
SPORTSNET.
THAT SHOULD BE LIKE A MILLION
DOLLARS.
>> JOIN ME IN SUNDAY NIGHT
BASEBALL IN THE BOOTH.
>> YOU CAN JOIN ME AND WE'LL
MAKE A PUPPET --
>> LEAST FAVORITE -- IN SOUTH
BEACH.
>> BID NOW AT E-BAY.COM/ESPN.
>>> AS HE SAIDS THE AUCTION
INCLUDES AMAZING EXPERIENCES
INCLUDING THESE FOOTBALL
EXPERIENCES.
GO TO E-BAY.COM/ESPN TO BID NOW
THROUGH JULY 10th.
ALL PROCEEDS BENEFIT THE V
FOUNDATION FOR CANCER RESEARCH.
>>> IF YOU WEREN'T WITH US IN
THE LAST SEGMENT, WE HAD
BREAKING NEWS ON EZEKIEL HE WILL
JOT.
HE WILL NOT FACE A PUNISHMENT
FOR A RECENT ROLE INVOLVING A
SECURITY GUARD.
HE DID NOT VIOLATE THE PERSONAL
CONDUCT POLICY SO NO SUSPENSION
FOR ELLIOTT, MUCH MORE ON THAT
THROUGHOUT THE DAY ON ESPN.
>> BIG NEWS YESTERDAY IN THE
OTHER KIND OF FOOTBALL.
U.S. WOMEN'S SOCCER TEAM BEATING
ENGLAND IN THE SEMIFINALS AT THE
WORLD CUP.
SINCE THAT TEAM CAN'T SEEM TO DO
ANYTHING, PART OF THE STORY IS
ALEX MORGAN'S TEA SIPPING
CELEBRATION FOLLOWING WHAT
TURNED OUT TO BE AT GAME WINNING
GOAL.
THE CELEBRATION -- HOWEVER YOU
FEEL ABOUTT IT'S GOT US THINKING
ABOUT SITUATIONS IN THE NFL
WHERE PEOPLE CELEBRATE AND KIND
OF TAILOR THEIR CELEBRATIONS A
LITTLE BIT TO THE OPPONENT.
WEEK FOUR OF THE YEAR 2000,
49ers AND COWBOYS, CELEBRATES A
TOUCHDOWN BY POSING ON THE
DALLAS STAR.
WAS THAT A HIT AT THE COWBOYS?
I COULDN'T TELL.
>> I LOVED IT, MAN.
>> WEEK TEN, DOLPHINS/PACKERS,
SACK OF AARON RODGERS.
KNOCKS HIM WITH THE DISCOUNT
DOUBLE-CHECK.
>> IF YOU'RE GOING TO DITCH
THEM, YOU GOT TO BE ABLE TO TAKE
IT.
>> BAKER MAYFIELD, OKLAHOMA,
COLLEGE FOOTAGE.
OKLAHOMA, OHIO STATE, DEFEATS
THE BUCKEYES.
PLANTS THE OU FLAG IN THE OHIO
STATE LOGO AT MIDFIELD.
AGAIN, NOT REAL SUBTLE.
2011, NFC WILDCARD GAME.
I WAS THERE.
FALCONS/GIANTS, AKIM NICKS
CATCHES A TOUCHDOWN PASS AND
DOES THE DIRTY BIRD DANCE.
I THOUGHT HE WAS TOO YOUNG TO
KNOW THAT.
DID HIS RESEARCH BEFORE THE
GAME.
>>> WEEK 10, PANTHERS/BRONCOS.
MILLER SACKS CAM NEWTON AND DOES
HIS SUPERMAN.
HE PRACTICED THAT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> DOUBLE STRUT THERE.
>> T.O. AGAIN.
WEEK 8, 2004.
EAGLES/RAVENS, TERRELL OWENS
CATCHES A TOUCHDOWN PASS AND
THREE GAME DANCE.
THAT'S GOOD.
>> I LOVE T.O.
>> IF YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE HIM
DO IT, THEN YOU BETTER STOP HIM.
YOU KNOW HE PRACTICED THAT.
>> OF COURSE.
YOU FRONT OFFICE GUYS IN YOUR
OFFICE OR WHATEVER, THESE GUYS
ARE IN THE LOCKER ROOM THINKING
OF ALL TYPES TO DO ON GAMEDAY.
I LOVED IT, MAN.
>> DID YOU KNOW THEY WERE DOING
THAT DOWN THERE?
>> COME ON.
DON'T BE A LAME.
WE'RE TRYING TO HAVE FUN OUT
HERE.
THIS IS A SPORT.
WE'RE TRYING TO HAVE FUN.
>> THE NFL HAS ALLOWED
CELEBRATIONS RECENTLY.
BUT THEY DON'T LIKE THE DIRECT
TAUNTING OF OPPONENTS.
WHERE IS THE LINE?
>> LISTEN, FOR ME IT'S
COMPETITION.
IT'S COMPETITION FOR ME.
I KNOW EVERYONE IS GOING TO TALK
ABOUT SPORTSMANSHIP.
I'VE BEEN UNDER THE IMPRESSION,
IF YOU DON'T WANT PEOPLE TO
CELEBRATE AND TALK TRASH, STOP
THEM.
STOP THEM.
PLAIN AND SIMPLE.
>> WHEN AT THE CELEBRATE AS A
TEAM, IT'S GREAT.
THE LAST COUPLE YEARS THERE'S
BEEN CREATIVE CELEBRATIONS GOING
BACK TO THE STEELERS, BENCH
PRESSING.
WHEN IT'S THE TEAM, I'M ALL FOR
IT.
>> SPOKEN LIKE A TRUE GENERAL
MANAGER.
>> YOU GUYS ARE ALL PRACTICING
YOUR CELEBRATIONS IN THE LOCKER
ROOM.
>>> COMING UP ON "NFL LIVE,"
MORE ON SDPLEEK YELL ELLIOTT.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT SOME MORE ON
"NFL LIVE."
(Danny)
Let me get this straight.
After a long day of hard work...
...you have to do more work?
Every day you're nearly fried
to a crisp, professionally!
Can someone turn on the AC?!
No? Oh right...
...'cause there isn't any.
Here-
(VO)
Automatically sort your expenses
and save over 40 hours a month.
Without you,
we wouldn't have electricity.
Our hobby would be
going to bed early.
(VO)
You earned it, we're here to
make sure you get it.
(Danny)
It's time to get yours!
(VO)
QUICKBOOKS. BACKING YOU.
The ant mindlessly marches on.
Carrying up to 50 times it's
body weight.
It never questions
the tasks at hand.
But this year, there's a more
thrilling path to follow.
(Father)
Kids...
...Change of plans!
(VO)
Defy the laws of human nature...
...at the summer of Audi sales
event
Get exceptional offers now!
>>> RECAPPING OURUR BREAKINING
TODAY ON "NFL LIVE."
COWBOYS RUNNING BACK, EZEKIEL
ELLIOTT WILL NOT FACE PUNISHMENT
FOR HIS ROLE IN A RECENT
INCIDENT WITH A SECURITY GUARD
IN LAS VEGAS.
ELLIOTT MET WITH COMMISSIONER
ROGER GOODELL FOR A COUPLE OF
HOURS TUESDAY THIS WEEK AND WAS
INFORMED HE WOULD NOT BE
SUSPENDED.
THE NFL RELEASED A STATEMENT
EXPLAINING IT, BASICALLY SAYS
THEY FOUND HE DID NOT VIOLATE
THE PERSONAL CONDUCT POLICY, BUT
THEY HOPE THAT HE CONTINUES TO
STAY OUT OF THESE SITUATIONS IN
THE FUTURE.
DAMIAN, YOUR THOUGHTS?
>> WELL, I MEAN, MY BIGGEST
THING IS DOES ZEKE GROW FROM
HERE?
THIS IS THE SECOND TIME GOING TO
NEW YORK.
THE FIRST TIME, I BELIEVE IT WAS
A SIX-GAME SUSPENSION.
THIS TIME HE GOT OFF WITH NO
SUSPENSION, BUT YOU WOULD THINK
THAT AT THIS POINT NOW, IT'S
TIME FOR YOU TO GROW AND MATURE
AND PUT YOURSELF IN COMPROMISING
SITUATIONS BECAUSE, AGAIN AS A
VETERAN, I'M DEPENDENT ON YOU.
I NEED -- GUYS IN THE LOCKER
ROOM NEED ALL HANDS ON DECK.
I WANT TO SEE MORE GROWTH AND
MATURITY OUT OF ZEKE ELLIOTT.
>> I TOTALLY AGREE.
YOU TAKE THAT A STEP FURTHER
WITH THE CONTRACT SITUATION IF
HE'S BEHAVING WITHOUT THAT BIG
DEAL, $45 MILLION GUARANTEED,
FROM AN ORGANIZATION STANDPOINT
WHAT, IS HE GOING TO BE LIKE
ONCE HE HAS THAT MONEY?
NOT ONLY DO I HAVE PAUSE FOR
CONCERN TO DO ANY DEAL, BUT IF
AND WHEN WE GET TO THAT POINT,
NOW I'M GOING TO REALLY WANT TO
MAKE SURE THAT THE STRUCTURE IS
APPROPRIATE WHERE WILL
GUARANTEED MONEY, CERTAINLY IF
HE GETS HURT PLAYING FOOTBALL.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE THE
TIEBLT -- IF THERE'S A THIRD
BUMP IN THE ROAD IN TERMS OF
ANYTHING OFF THE FIELD.
HE'S PUT HIMSELF IN THAT
POSITION.
HE'S HAD TEAMMATES THAT PLAYED
VERY WELL, LIKE THE STARTING
QUARTERBACK, DAK PRESCOTT AND
HANDLED THEIR BUSINESS OFF THE
FIELD.
HE'S DONE THIS TO HIMSELF.
NOT ONLY WOULD I CONSIDER
PAUSING AND NOT DOING A
LONG-TERM DEAL IF AND WHEN WE
GOT TO THE POINT, THE STRUCTURE
OF THE CONTRACT WOULD BE -- AS
AN ORGANIZATION, SOMETHING ELSE
HAPPENS, I WANT TO CUT THE
PLAYER AND NOT HAVE TO PAY HIM
MORE MONEY.
>> THAT'S THE KEY POINT.
IF SOMETHING ELSE HAPPENS, HE
WAS WARNED WHEN HE WAS SUSPENDED
IN 2017.
HE SEEMS -- DAMIAN SAID HE GOT
LUCKY BUT THEY COULD HAVE
SUSPENDED UNDER THE PERSONAL
CONDUCT POLICY GIVEN THAT
WARNING.
BUT I MEAN, THIS IS A
TRANSCENDENT PLAYER WHO LED THE
LEAGUE IN RUSHING TWO OF HIS
THREE YEARS, LED THE LEAGUE IN
RUSHING THE YEAR HE WAS
SUSPENDED.
TO GET TO THE POINT YOU RELEASE
HIM, THAT HAS TO BE A PRETTY
EXTREME SITUATION, DOESN'T IT?
>> LISTEN, WE KNOW HOW THE
LEAGUE WORKS.
THE MORE TALENTED YOU ARE, THE
MORE OPPORTUNITIES YOU GET.
YOU SAID IT PERFECTLY, THE
TRANSCENDENT TALENT.
ONE OF THE BEST PLAYERS WE HAVE
IN OUR LEAGUE.
BUT AGAIN, IF YOU'RE NOT
AVAILABLE, WHAT GOOD ARE YOU TO
THE TEAM?
AGAIN, YOU WOULD LIKE TO SEE
ZEKE ELLIOTT MATURE AND GET PAST
THESE INCIDENCES THAT WE'VE SEEN
FROM HIM, THE THREE YEARS PLUS
OF WHATEVER HE'S BEEN IN THE
NATIONAL FOOTBALL LEAGUE SO HE
CAN HELP HIS TEAM GET TO WHERE
THEY WANT TO GO.
>> PRODUCTION EQUALS TOLERANCE.
BECAUSE HE'S PRODUCED AT SUCH A
HIGH LEVEL, HE'S BEEN A HIGH
LEVEL POWER.
AT SOME POINT THAT EQUALS OUT.
HOPEFULLY, HE CAN LEARN FROM
THIS, GROW AND PUT ALL THIS
BEHIND HIM AND HELP THE COWBOY
TRY TO WIN A SUPER BOWL.
>> EZEKIEL ELLIOTT REPRESENTS
THE BIG NFL NEWS OF THE DAY.
ON ESPN, THOUGH, WE DON'T LIMIT
OURSELVES TO NFL.
OUR NEXT CANADIAN FOOTBALL
LEAGUE MATCHUP ON ESPN PLUS IS
TOMORROW NIGHT.
IT'S A FORMAT BETWEEN THE TIGER
CATS AND THE MONTREAL AL OWE
WETS.
THAT WILL BE AT 7:30 EASTERN.
>> EVERYBODY IS GOING TO SAY WE
COULD BE AND SHOULD BE SUPER
BOWL CONTENDERS.
>> WHO WOULDN'T ASPIRE TO BE THE
PATRIOTS.
WHO WOULDN'T WANT TO BE 11-5?
>> I WANT TO GET TO BE WHAT THE
PATRIOTS ARE.
>> THE CLEVELAND BROWNS GOING
FROM THE HUNTER TO THE HUNTED
NOW.
>> OH, WHAT A CATCH BY NJOKU.
>> I FEEL LIKE A LITTLE KID, THE
EXCITEMENT THAT I HAVE.
>> THEY HAVE NO EXCUSE FOR NOT
BEING A CONTENDER IN THE AFC.
THEY HAVE NO EXCUSE.
>> CLEVELAND BROWNS DAVID NJOKU
GETTING READY FOR A HIGHLY
ANTICIPATED SEASON IN CLEVELAND.
DAVID, WE'VE SEEN SOME OF WHAT
YOU GUYS CAN DO.
CERTAINLY INDIVIDUALLY.
WHAT WE HAVEN'T SEEN IS FREDDIE
KITCHENS AS A HEAD COACH.
TELL US WHAT FREDDIE IS LIKE NOW
THAT HE'S THE HEAD COACH?
>> FREDDIE IS A GREAT HEAD
COACH.
I BELIEVE HE'S A PLAYER'S COACH
IF THAT MAKES ANY SENSE.
HE KNOWS WHAT IT TAKES FOR US TO
DO WHAT WE HAVE TO DO.
WE KNOW AS WELL.
EVERYTHING TOGETHER.
HOPEFULLY GOOD THINGS HAPPEN.
SO WE'LL SEE.
>> BRINGING SOME STABILITY TO
THAT SITUATION THIS YEAR.
OBVIOUSLY, LAST YEAR THERE
WASN'T.
WHAT WAS IT LIKE GOING THROUGH
THAT LAST YEAR WITH ALL THE
TURMOIL AND THE FIRINGS AND ALL
THAT STUFF IN MID-SEASON WITH
THE COACHING STAFF.
HOW TOUGH WAS THAT?
>> YES, IT WAS A BUNCH OF
TURMOIL.
HAVING YOUR HEAD COACH AND O.C.
FIRED.
IT BROUGHT A LOT OF QUESTIONS
AND CURIOSITY, BUT I FEEL LIKE
AS A TEAM AND AS LIKE THE
PLAYERS, WE TOOK IT UPON
OURSELVES TO, YOU KNOW, TO COME
TOGETHER AND FOCUS ON HOW WE
HAVE TO FINISH THIS YEAR OR THIS
PAST YEAR STRONG.
AND I BELIEVE WE DID JUST THAT.
AND I BELIEVE THIS UPCOMING YEAR
WILL BE REALLY SPECIAL.
>> A LOT OF TIMES PLAYERS SAY
THE FRONT OFFICE STUFF, DOESN'T
AFFECT THE LOCKER ROOM.
WERE THERE HARD FEELINGS.
IT SEEMS LIKE BAKER MAYFIELD HAD
THINGS TO SAY ABOUT THE
SITUATION.
WAS THAT A WIDESPREAD FEELING?
>> THERE'S NO HARD FEELINGS.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, EVERYONE
MUST UNDERSTAND THAT THIS IS A
BUSINESS.
YOU HAVE TO TREAT IS AS SUCH.
THERE'S NO HARD FEELINGS.
WHATEVER HAPPENED, HAPPENED.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
WE'RE FOCUSED ON WHAT WE HAVE TO
DO TO REACH OUR GOAL.
>> YOU DIDN'T LACK FOR TALENT ON
THE OFFENSIVE SIDE OF THE BALL
TO BEGIN WITH.
ODELL BECKHAM ESTABLISHED AS ONE
OF THE TOP RECEIVING OPTIONS IN
THE ENTIRE LEAGUE.
WHAT HAVE YOU SEEN FROM HIM IN
TERMS OF WHAT HE'S SHOWN YOU ON
THE FIELD AND WHAT KIND OF
TEAMMATE HE IS.
>> YEAH.
ODELL IS AN ELITE ATHLETE.
WE'RE ACTUALLY ALL TOGETHER
YESTERDAY, JARVIS, HOLLYWOOD
HIGGINS, ME, BAKER AND A BUNCH
OF OTHER GUYS.
DEMETRIUS HARRIS, BROWN, WE WERE
WORKING ON TIMING AND
EVERYTHING.
WHEN IT COMES TO US AS A UNIT,
WE ARE VERY DANGEROUS IS THE
WORD TO SAY.
>> HOW ABOUT PERSONAL GOALS FOR
YOU?
OBVIOUSLY, YOU'RE A YOUNG PLAYER
STILL GROWING IN THIS LEAGUE,
WHAT DO YOU LOOK AT AND SAY
HERE'S WHAT I WANT TO ACCOMPLISH
GOING FORWARD?
>> AS LONG AS I FEELEY GAVE IT
MY ALL, I WORKED TO MY ABILITY,
I'M CONTENT WITH THIS YEAR.
I DON'T REALLY HAVE ANY NUMBERS.
I WAS MESSING AROUND SAYING 20
TOUCHDOWNS, BUT HONESTLY
SPEAKING, I WANT TO HAVE A GREAT
YEAR.
WE WANT TO WIN AND WIN AS MUCH
AS POSSIBLE AND OBVIOUSLY GO TO
THE SUPER BOWL AND THAT'S WHAT
THE BIG TERM GOAL.
>> WHEN YOU'RE LOOKING TO
IMPROVE YOUR GAME, IS THERE
SOMETHING YOU'RE SPECIFICALLY
WORKING ON YOU'RE TRYING TO GET
BETTER AT?
>> OF COURSE.
HONESTLY, SPEAKING, I'M WORKING
ON ALL ASPECTS.
I DON'T BELIEVE I MASTERED
ANYTHING REGARDING THE TIGHT END
POSITION JUST YET.
IT'S REALLY EVERYTHING THAT I
WANT TO WORK ON TO BETTER MYSELF
AS AN OVERALL TIGHT END AND
PLAYER.
>> WE'RE GOING TO ASK YOU A
PERSONAL QUESTION IF THAT'S ALL
RIGHT.
YOU HAVE EIGHT SIBLINGS, IS THAT
CORRECT?
YOU'RE ONE OF NINE BROTHERS AND
SISTERS.
>> CORRECT.
>> YOUR OLDER BROTHER, INNOCENT,
STUDYING TO BE A NEUROLOGIST.
WHAT KINDS OF CONVERSATIONS --
>> NEUROSURGEON.
>> EXCUSE ME.
MORE IMPRESSIVE.
WHAT KIND OF CONVERSATIONS DO
YOU HAVE ABOUT FOOTBALL AND THE
DANGERS OF YOUR CHOSEN
PROFESSION.
>> OBVIOUSLY, HE UNDERSTANDS AS
WELL AS I DO THAT FOOTBALL IS A
DANGEROUS SPORT.
I HAVE TWO YOUNGER BROTHERS, HE
PLAYS AT MIAMI RIGHT NOW.
AT THE UNIVERSITY OF MIAMI AND
MY YOUNGEST ONE CHARLES NJOKU,
HE JUST ARRIVED AT UCLA TO START
HIS SUMMER PROGRAM AS A
RECEIVER.
THEY BOTH PLAY RECEIVERS.
WE ALL UNDERSTAND THAT FOOTBALL
IS OBVIOUSLY A DANGEROUS SPORT.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME, IT IS OUR
PASSION.
WE WORK EXTREMELY HARD TO BE THE
BEST WE CAN BE.
MY OLDEST BROTHER, INNOCENT, HE
UNDERSTANDS THAT.
HE LOVES OUR PASSION FOR IT.
BUT OBVIOUSLY, HE'S THE ONE
SAYING, BE CAREFUL.
MAKE SURE YOU'RE SAFE AND
EVERYTHING.
YEAH.
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT.
>> I GUESS IT CAN BE HANDY TO
HAVE SOMEBODY LIKE THAT IN THE
FAMILY.
>> I ALWAYS TELL HIM THAT ONCE
THE THREE OF US ARE DONE PLAYING
FOOTBALL, HE HAS TO TAKE CARE OF
US IN ALL SHAPE AND FORM.
IT'S ALL LOVE AT THE END OF THE
DAY.
>> HOPEFULLY HE DOESN'T HAVE
MUCH TO DO IN THAT REGARD.
DAVID, THANKS SO MUCH FOR
JOINING US, BEST OF LUCK.
>> MY PLEASURE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> BAKER MAYFIELD, OVEN NJOKU,
JARVIS LANDRY, RECEIVER ALONG
WITH KAREEM HUNT IN THE
BACKFIELD WHEN HUNT'S SUSPENSION
IS OVER.
THOSE FIVE COMBINED FOR 41
TOUCHDOWNS AND 641 TOUCHES.
SO I GUESS THE BIG QUESTION,
GOOD PROBLEM TO HAVE, IS THERE
ENOUGH TO GO AROUND IN THAT
CLEVELAND BROWNS OFFENSE?
>> I LOT A LOT OF PIECES.
A GREAT COLLECTION OF TALENT.
THAT'S WHY IT FALLS ON FREDDIE
KITCHENS.
THE CLEVELAND BROWNS ARE IN A
POSITION THEY HAVEN'T BEEN IN A
LONG TIME.
THEY ARE THE HUNTED.
IT'S A TOTALLY DIFFERENT
POSITION TO BE IN GOING FORWARD
IN THE SEASON.
THEY'LL BE ON PRIMETIME A LOT.
LET'S SEE WHAT THEY CAN DO WITH
IT.
>> THE ONE THING WE DIDN'T SEE
ON THE GRAPHIC WAS THE LACK OF
EXPERIENCE OF THEIR HEAD COACH
FREDDIE KITCHENS.
I BELIEVE ONE DAY KITCHENS WILL
BE A HEAD COACH.
ONE YEAR AGO, GUYS, HE WAS A
POSITION COACH.
IT'S LIKE LEARNING HOW TO DRIVE
A CAR GOING 90 MILES AN HOUR IN
THE LEFT-HAND LANE AND IN THE
DIVISION, YOU HAVE JOHN HARBAUGH
AND MIKE TOMLIN SINCE 2007.
MIKE TOMLIN HAS THE SECOND MOST
WINS IN THE NFL.
JOHN HARBAUGH HAS THE SIXTH MOST
WINS.
FROM A COACHING STANDPOINT, HOW
FREDDIE KITCHENS CAN MELD THAT
GROUP WILL BE INTERESTING TO
WATCH.
>> INTERESTING TO WATCH WHAT WE
HAVE COMING STILL ON "NFL LIVE"
TODAY.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE MORE EZEKIEL
ELLIOTT SITUATION.
COWBOYS RUNNING BACK NOT
SUSPENDED BY THE NFL FOR HIS
RECENT INCIDENT AND BECAUSE
TOMORROW IS INDEPENDENCE DAY,
WE'RE GOING TO TALK ABOUT THE
GREAT INDEPENDENT NFL PLAYS OF
ALL-TIME.
STICK AROUND TO SEE WHAT THAT'S
ALL ABOUT.
New for summer,
it's Bud Light Lemon Tea.
Brewed with REAL lemon peels
and aged on REAL tea leaves.
Yes, it's real.
No, you're not dreaming.
Hey, don't do that.
♪  ♪
In every trip,
there's room for more
p,
than just the business
theryou came for.more
♪♪
Whether that's keeping up
with what you always do...
or training
for something
you've never done before.
That's room
for possibility.
you've never done before.
That's room
for possibility.
♪♪
Look! Make a wish!
I wish for a Biggie
Bag from Wendy's.
I wish everyone loved each
other and was always...
That's a great wish, Jimmy.
Get a Bacon Double stack with
a quarter pound of fresh beef,
nuggets, fries and a
drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
They made the original hot
(hot hot)?
♪Here's a shake up♪
♪My Hot Flamin's
mixin' with Doritos♪
♪(Hello)♪
♪Talkin bout how far back we go♪
♪Way way way way back♪
♪(Is it me you're looking for)♪
♪I don't care about that♪
♪I ain't sharin' my snacks♪
The Original, now it's hot.
So I can buy from
Enterprise Car Sales and you'll
take ANY trade-in?
That's right!
Great!
Here you go...
Well, it does need
to be a vehicle.
But - I need this out of
my house.
(VO) With fair, transparent
value for every trade-in...
Enterprise makes it easy.
>>> UFC 239 IN THE LAS VEGAS.
TWO OF THE GREATEST UFC
CHAMPIONS DEFENDING THEIR
TITLES.
BATTLED SANTOS AND AMANDA NUNEZ
TAKES ON -- IN THE CO-MAIN
EVENTS ON PAY-PER-VIEW STARTING
AT 10:00 EASTERN, 7:00 PACIFIC.
THE MAIN CARD, GO TO ESPN
PLUS.COM/PPV.
DOWNLOAD THE ESPN APP IF YOU'RE
WATCHING ON YOUR MOBILE DEVICE.
TONIGHT WE HAVE THE GET OFF NBA
FREE AGENCY SPECIAL WITH KEVIN
THAT GANDHI AND -- THEY'LL HAVE
THE LATEST ON KAWHI LEONARD AND
JOHN BONES JONES ANSWERS THE
QUESTIONS AHEAD ON SATURDAY.
AMERICAN COCOA GAUFF HAS HER
SECOND ACT.
RECAPPING OUR BEAK BREAKING NEWS
HERE ON "NFL LIVE."
EZEKIEL ELLIOTT, THE COWBOYS
RUNNING BACK WILL NOT BE
PUNISHED.
THE LEAGUE DID NOT -- FOUND HE
DID NOT VIOLATE THE PERSONAL
CONDUCT POLICY IN AN INCIDENT
INVOLVING A SECURITY GUARD IN
LAS VEGAS RECENTLY.
THE NFL INTERVIEWED HIM ON
TUESDAY AND SPOKE HIS GIRLFRIEND
WHO WAS THERE AT THE TIME OF THE
INCIDENT AND HAVE DETERMINED
THAT HE WILL NOT FACE
PUNISHMENT.
GUYS, WE'VE HAD A LOT OF
CONVERSATION ABOUT THIS.
BUT ONE REAL QUICK SORT OF
WRAP-UP ON THE UPSHOT OF EZEKIEL
ELLIOTT.
>> FLIRTED WITH FIRE AGAIN.
BEEN FORTUNATE.
NOW IT'S FOCUSED ON THE UPCOMING
SEASON.
>> FOR THE DALLAS COWBOYS, THIS
IS A REALLY IMPORTANT DAY.
LET'S GET IT WRAPPED UP, PUT IT
BEHIND US.
IT'S BEFORE JULY 4th.
WE CAN GET TO TRAINING CAMP.
IT'S ONE LESS DISTRACTION TO
WORRY ABOUT.
NOW WE CAN FOCUS ON THE
PHILADELPHIA EAGLES AND TRYING
TO WIN THE NFC EAST THIS YEAR.
>> MIKE, THANKS FOR THE HELP
WITH THE SEGUE.
TOMORROW IS JULY 4th.
IT'S CALLED INDEPENDENCE DAY.
BEFORE YOU FIRE UP YOUR GRILLS,
DIG YOUR FEET INTO THAT, WE WANT
TO TAKE YOU INTO THE INDEPENDENT
PLAY IN NFL HISTORY.
YOU CAN PLAY WHERE ONE GUY DID
IT ALL OR INDEPENDENTLY.
HOW ABOUT PAT McAFEE AND THE
COLTS.
2014 AGAINST THE TEXANS.
RECOVERS IT.
>> SMART PLAY.
>> HALL OF FAME GAME.
TITANS PUBLIC TELEVISIONER A.J.
TRA PASS OWE.
TAKES IT ALL THE WAY.
NUMBER 8, 1997, VIKINGS.
PANTHERS, VIKINGS QUARTERBACK
BRAD JOHNSON THROWS THE PASS.
BACK TO HIM AND, SURE, I'LL TAKE
IT.
HE'S GOING TO RUN IT RIGHT IN
FOR A TOUCHDOWN ON HIS OWN.
>> GREEN LIKED IT.
>> UNDER RATED CAREER
QUARTERBACK.
>> NUMBER 7, MARCUS.
MARIOTA, THE 2017 WOILD CARD
GAME.
REMEMBER THAT ONE TOO.
MARIOTA SCRAMBLES, THROWS.
BUT IT'S NOT -- DARRELLE REVIS,
HE'LL SCORE IT HIMSELF.
BIG COMEBACK THAT DAY FOR
TENNESSEE.
NUMBER 6, 2017, 49ers AGAINST
THE BEARS.
THE PUNT AND TARIK COHEN CORRALS
IT.
TAKES IT FROM THE 40.
HE'S NOT GOING TO LET HIMSELF
GET TACKLED HERE.
>> HE'S OUT-RUNNING THE
COVERAGE.
>> HE STUCK TO HIS PLAN.
IT'S GOING TO PAY OFF.
>> HIM AND GRANT ARE TWO OF THE
MOST DYNAMIC PLAYERS IN THE OPEN
FIELD.
THEY'RE FAST AND QUICK AND HARD
TO TACKLE.
>> 2002, BUCKS -- MICHAEL VICK.
PLAY ACTION.
GETS OUTSIDE.
YOU KNOW HE'S GOING TO CATCH IT.
>> THIS IS LIKE A WALK-OFF HOME
RUN HERE.
THIS WAS IT.
POTENTIAL PLAY.
>> OVERTIME GAME.
THIS IS MY PERSONAL FAVORITE,
GUYS.
NUMBER 4, 1991, COWBOYS LAND THE
ONE AND ONLY BARRY SANDERS
RUSHING UP THE SIDE AND SOMEHOW
GETS OUT OF THIS MESS.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO --
>> TALK ABOUT STEPPING ON A
DIME.
>>RY RIDICULOUS.
>> BARRY DESERVED IT.
>> DEON SANDERS.
HE DROPS THE PUNT.
TAKES IT BACK.
THIS IS HIS FIRST PUNT RETURN
TOUCHDOWN.
I DO NOT KNOW IF HE ALSO PLAYED
BASEBALL FOR THE ATLANTA BRAVES
THAT NIGHT.
I KNOW HE DID AT SOME POINT.
VERY VERSATILE.
INDEPENDENT KIND OF PLAYER.
DEION SANDERS.
HE'S GONE ALL THE WAY.
>> HE'S GOING TO HIGH STEP IT IN
THE END ZONE.
>> ON THE INDEPENDENT PLAYS.
>> NUMBER 2, A SUPER BOWL PLAY.
SUPER BOWL XLIII, YOU REMEMBER
IT IF YOU'RE A STEELERS FAN.
FIRST AND GOAL FOR THE CARDS.
KURT WARNER IS INTERCEPTED BY
JAMES HARRISON.
HE'S GOING TO RUN IT ALL THE WAY
BACK.
>> WHEN HE CATCHES THE BALL, NO
WAY TO SCORE.
>> THERE'S TOO MANY GUYS TO
TRACK DOWN.
>> THE INSTAGRAM WORKOUTS.
HOW DO YOU LET HIM UP THE FOUL
LINE.
JUST PUSH HIM OUT.
>> HARD TO PUSH IT OUT.
>> OFFENSIVE LINEMAN TRYING TO
RUN IT OUT.
>> 2011 NFC WILDCARD GAME.
SAINTS/SEAHAWKS, ON IT OWN RUNS.
STIFF ARMED.
EAST QUAKE, EAST MODE.
THAT WAS WHAT, 7-9 TEEMT.