KNOW HOW MUCH BETTER HE CAN BE
AFTER THESE LAST COUPLE
INJURIES.
>> THIS IS IRRELEVANT.
>> THIS IS WHO HAS THE MOST -- A
SMALLER DEAL.
>> HE'S NOT -- WELL, WE HERD
ADRIAN TALK ABOUT IT.
THERE'S NO INTEREST.
WHEN THERE'S NO INTEREST GUESS
WHAT KIND OF DEA RE AVAILABLE
TO YOU, THE MINIMUM EXCEPTION.
PUT ALL 30 TEAM THERE IS.
>> VERY INTERESTING.
WELL, WE HAVE TO SEE.
WE MIGHT KNOW MORE BY TONIGHT.
RIGHT?
WE COULD KNOW ABOUT KAWHI AND
BOOGIE BY TONIGHT.
COME HANG OUT WITH US, 7:00 ON
ES
♪♪
>>> THIS TUESDAY EDITION OF "NFL
LIVE."
JUJU SMITH-SCHUSTER JOINS US
ABOUT TAKING OVER AS THE
STEELERS TOP RECEIVER AND WHAT
HIS RELATIONSHIP WITH ANTONIO
BROWN LOOKS LIKE NOW.
WE HIGHLIGHT SOME OF THE STARS
THAT ARE NOMINATED FOR ESPYS
INCLUDING A LOOK BACK AT DREW
BREES' RECORD-BREAKING MONDAY
NIGHT FOOTBALL PERFORMANCE.
PLUS WE HAND OUT OUR OWN AWARDS
FOR THE PLAYER WITH THE BEST
HIGHLIGHTS.
PATRICK MAHOMES, SAQUON OR KYLER
IN THE RUNNING.
WHO WILL BE CROWNED YOUR
HIGHLIGHT KING.
HAPPY TO HAVE YOU WITH US.
HOLIDAY WEEK.
WENDI NIX, DIANNA RUSSINI,
VICTOR CRUZ AND MIKE TANNENBAUM
AND WE'LL START WITH NEWS
REGARDING IZZY GILL ELLIOTT.
THE DALLAS COWBOY RUNNING BACK
EXPECTED TO MEET WITH THE
COMMISSIONER TODAY IN NEW YORK
CITY REGARDING A MAY INCIDENT IN
LAS VEGAS.
THE MEETING COMES AFTER AN
INCIDENT AT A LAS VEGAS MUSIC
FESTIVAL WHERE HE HAD A
CONFRONTATION WITH A SECURITY
GUARD BRIEFLY DETAINED BUT NEVER
ARRESTED OR CHARGED IN THE
INCIDENT.
NEVERTHELESS, THE COMMISSIONER
WANTS TO HEAR HIM OUT.
DIANNA, WHAT MORE CAN YOU TELL
US.
>> AT THIS POINT WE DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT IS GOING ON IN THAT
MEETING BUT THEY ARE MEETING IN
MANHATTAN TO DISCUSS ZEKE'S
BEHAVIOR IN THAT LAS VEGAS
INCIDENT.
JERRY JONES, OF COURSE, HAS
STOOD BY HIS RUNNING BACK SAYING
THAT HE DOESN'T SEE ANYTHING
WRONG WITH WHAT HE SAW ON
VIDEOTAPE, AGAIN, ZEKE IN THOSE
HANDCUFFS AND THEN THOSE
HANDCUFFS WERE REMOVED.
HE COULD STILL FACE PUNISHMENT
IN GOODELL DECIDES HE VIOLATED
THE LEAGUE'S PERSONAL CONDUCT
POLICY AND THAT'S WHAT THIS MEET
SOMETHING TO DISCUSS.
BUT AS OF NOW WE ARE NOT SURE
WHAT THE FUTURE HOLES BUT THOSE
THAT I'VE SPOKEN TO WITH THE
COWBOYS ORGANIZATION STRONGLY
FEEL CONFIDENT THAT ZEKE WILL
NOT FACE A SUSPENSION IN THIS
BECAUSE OF THIS INCIDENT.
>> MIKE, AS A GM, I KNOW YOU
HAVE PLAYERS WHO HAD
FACE-TO-FACE MEETINGS WITH THE
COMMISSIONER WHO HAD HEARINGS OR
DUE DILIGENCE.
WHAT'S YOUR TAKE GENTLEMAN.
>> DESPITE HOW THE COWBOYS ARE
FEELING A SUSPENSION CERTAINLY
IS IN PLAY.
WE HAVE TO REMEMBER UNDER THE
PERSONAL CONDUCT POLICY, A
PLAYER CAN BE SUSPENDED EVEN
THOUGH THERE MAY NOT BE CHRISMAN
CHARGES AND THE FACT THAT
EZEKIEL ELLIOTT IS MEETING IN
PERSON WITH THE COMMISSIONER
SIGNALS TO ME THAT A SUSPENSION
ALBEIT ONE GAME, TWO GAMES COULD
BE IN PLAY HERE AND HE WAS SENT
TO NEW YORK FOR A REASON SO
WE'LL SEE HOW IT PLAYS OUT IN
THE COMING DAYS BUT HIS PRIOR
BEHAVIOR WILL CERTAINLY BE A
FACTOR IN THEIR ASSESSMENT.
>> WELL, LET'S SHIFT GEARS TO
BETWEEN THE LINES.
VICTOR, HOW IMPORTANT IS THE RUN
GAME TO THIS CURRENT DALLAS
COWBOYS TEAM.
>> HUGE, ESPECIALLY EZEKIEL
ELLIOTT.
HE'S BEEN THE FOCAL POINT OF THE
OFFENSE YEAR IN AND YEAR OUT.
HANDING HIM THE FOOTBALL BEHIND
THAT FANTASTIC OFFENSIVE LINE, I
MEAN, HE IS IN MY OPINION THE
HEARTBEAT OF THAT OFFENSE.
OBVIOUSLY DAK IS THE LEADER.
BUT EZEKIEL MAKES HIM GO.
YOU GOT THE PLAY-ACTION PASS AND
EVERYTHING COMPLIMENTS THE
ATTRIBUTES SO IF HE'S THERE TO
MISS ANY SIGNIFICANT AMOUNT OF
TIME THE COWBOYS WOULD BE
LOOKING TO REPLACE THAT, YOU
KNOW, THOSE STATISTICS AND
NUMBERS THAT HE PUTS UP WEEK IN
AND WEEK OUT IN A DIFFERENT WAY.
>> YEAH, AND, VIC, YOU HIT THE
NAIL ON THE HEAD.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT DAK PRESCOTT
HIS PASS RATING CHANGED SO YOU
CAN SEE THE IMPORTANCE OF THE
RUNNING GAME, EZEKIEL ELLIOTT
OBVIOUSLY OPPOSING DEFENSES ARE
FOCUSING IN ON STOPPING EZEKIEL
ELLIOTT AND THAT'S A VERY
IMPACTFUL IN TERMS OF HIS IMPACT
ON DAK PRESCOTT'S PRODUCTION A
HUGE JUMP IN TERMS OF HIS PLAY
ACTION PRODUCTIVITY.
>> HUGE JUMP.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT DAK'S DEAL AND
WHEN IT MAY GET DONE.
THIS DLABS TEAM STACKS UP IN THE
DIVISION.
>> I THINK THEY'RE RIGHT THERE
AT THE TOP.
I THINK THEY'RE COMPETING
OBVIOUSLY THEM AND PHILADELPHIA
RIGHT THERE NECK AND NECK GOING
TO BE BATTLING IT OUT THROUGHOUT
THE SEASON BUT I THINK THEY GOT
ALL THE TOOLS.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THEM
DEFENSIVELY FROM THE DEFENSIVE
LINE BACK TO THE SECOND DRI
THEY'RE LOADED AT EACH POSITION
AND THEN OFFENSIVELY LIKE WE
JUST TALKED ABOUT, DAK, EZEKIEL
ELLIOTT, AMARI COOPER, RANDALL
COBB, I COULD GO ON FOR DAYS
WITH THIS BUT THEY HAVE ALL THE
TALENT, EXACTLY.
THEY GOT ALL OF THE TALENT NOT
TO MENTION --
>> NEW OFFENSIVE COORDINATOR.
>> WHICH OBVIOUSLY COMES FROM,
YOU KNOW, COLLEGE AND DOING
THOSE DIFFERENT THINGS SO HE'LL
PROVIDE SOME CREATIVITY THAT WE
PROBABLY HAVEN'T SEEN FROM
DIFFERENT TYPE OF PLAYS THAT WE
HAVEN'T SEEN NECESSARILY FROM
THE DALLAS COWBOYS.
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING WITH THE
EAGLES YOU'RE GOING WITH THE
DALLAS COWBOYS TO WIN THAT
DIVISION.
>> YES, UNFORTUNATELY, NOBODY IN
NEW YORK KILL ME.
>> THAT WAS VICTOR.
WHEN DOES DAK'S DEAL GET DONE?
DO WE SEE THAT DONE BEFORE THE
START OF THE SEASON?
>> I THINK THAT WILL GET DONE
BEFORE THE START OF THE SEASON.
EVEN TALKING TO PEOPLE IN THE
COWBOYS ORGANIZATION ABOUT THE
TIMING OF IT, IT'S FUNNY BECAUSE
JUST A FEW MONTHS AGO, THE WAY
IT WAS BEING EXPLAINED TO ME IT
WAS GOING TO BE A WHILE.
IT WASN'T GOING TO GET DONE AND
NOW IT SEEMS THAT I'M NOT SURE
WHERE THE PRESSURE IS COMING
FROM.
I DON'T KNOW WHY THEY'RE FEELING
THE PRESSURE BUT IN TERMS OF
TRYING TO GET IT DONE IT SEEMS
LIKE IT'S GOING TO BE A
PRIORITY.
>> THE PRESSURE COMES FROM WHAT
DAK'S DRAFT DAY DISAPPOINTMENT
WAS IS NOW BECOMING THE REALITY
OF A FREE AGENT OPPORTUNITY
BECAUSE HE WAS NOT A FIRST ROUND
PICK WHICH WAS A DISAPPOINTMENT
BUT HE'S IN THE FINAL YEAR OF
HIT CONTRACT SO UNLIKE GUYS LIKE
JARED GOFF AND CARSON WENTZ WHO
HAD THE ADDITIONAL FIFTH YEAR HE
COULD GET TO THE MARKET AND MAY
NOT BE A PERFECT PLAYER.
I'M A BELIEVE IN DAK PRESCOTT
NOT ONLY BECAUSE OF WHAT HE CAN
DO FROM A PASSING STANDPOINT BUT
THE PLAYS HE MAKES WITH HIS
LEGS, IF HE MADE IT TO THE OPEN
MARKET THE WAY KIRK COUSINS DID
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO HARD TO
SAY WHAT HE CAN GET.
HE CAN CERTAINLY GET FRAN CHRIST
BUT I CAN TELL YOU FROM AN
ORGANIZATION STANDPOINT WHEN YOU
USE THE FRANCHISE TAG THE LAST
POSITION YOU WANT TO USE IT ON
IS THE QUARTERBACK.
BECAUSE WHEN YOU HAVE A
FRANCHISE TAG, THAT MEANS THAT
THE PLAYER DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
THERE FOR THE OFF-SEASON
PROGRAM.
DOESN'T HAVE TO BE THERE FOR
TRAINING CAMP.
HE COULD COME IN THE TUESDAY
BEFORE OPENING DAY, SIGN THE
TAG, GET PAID FOR THE WHOLE
SEASON AND IT REALLY PUTS THE
OFFENSE AND ALL THOSE REPS YOU
DON'T HAVE TOGETHER, VIC SO THE
SENSE OF URGENCY IS COMING FROM
THE FACT THAT THIS PLAYER IS 16
GAMES AWAY FROM BECOMING A FREE
AGENT.
>> THAT QUARTERBACK ALSO FEELS
THAT PRESSURE.
I MEAN, THEY DON'T EVER REALLY
FEEL LIKE THEY BELONG.
WITH THE KIRK COUSINS SITUATION
IN WASHINGTON.
HE WAS ALWAYS OUT THERE PROVING
AND PROVING AND PROVING.
AND I REMEMBER TALKING TO HIM
ABOUT IT AND YOU COULD TELL IT
WAS --
>> WEIGHS ON HIM.
>> IT WAS LIKE THE WASHINGTON
REDSKINS ORGANIZATION WERE
LOOKING TO DATE AND DATE AND HE
WAS LOOKING FOR A RING.
HE WANTED TO GET MARRIED AND
WANTED TO FEEL THAT LOVE AND
NEVER DID.
FOR THE COWBOYS TO PUT THAT ON
DAK THAT MAY NOT WORK OUT FOR
THEM, YOU KNOW, IF THEY WANT TO
MAKE THAT WORK.
YOU KNOW WHAT HE'S MARRIED TO,
MONEY.
A LOT OF MONEY.
I AM NOT CRYING FOR KIRK COUSINS
BUT IT IS A POINT WELL MADE.
ALL RIGHT.
ANYWAY, CIRCLING BACK TO WHERE
WE STARTED ZEKE ELLIOTT AND THE
COWBOYS HOPING HE WILL NOT MISS
ANY TIME.
VIDEO SHOWS BROWNS RUNNING BACA
REAM HUNT BEING QUESTIONED BY
POLICE AFTER AN APPARENT
INCIDENT SATURDAY NIGHT.
THIS IS AT A CLEVELAND BAR.
THE VIDEO PUBLISHED BY TMZ
SPORTS SHOWS HUNT SPEAKING WITH
A NUMBER OF OFFICERS.
HE WAS NOT ARRESTED.
THEY DID NOT MAKE A POLICE
REPORT REGARDING THE INCIDENT.
THIS ACCORDING TO A SPOKESPERSON
TO CLEVELAND.COM.
STILL TO COME ON "NFL LIVE,"
STAR WIDE RECEIVER MR. SCHUSTER
IS JOINING US FROM ACROSS THE
POND IN LONDON.
SEE WHAT HE'S UP TO AND THE
SCHOOL OF A HIGH SCHOOL FOOTBALL
COACH BORN WITH ONE OF THE
RAREST CONDITIONS IN THE WORLD.
>> THERE'S DEFINITELY DOUBTERS
OUT THERE.
MY SON IS GETTING COACHED BY
QUARTERBACKS LIKE A GUY I DON'T
KNOW.
THAT LIGHTS A FIRE UNDER MY BUTT
AND PROBABLY GETS ME EXCITED TO
TRY TO PROVE PEOPLE WRONG ABOUT
IT.
That's the only circumstance to
which you would separate.
Can't imagine doing it
any other way.
This is Caitlin Dickerson from
The New York Times.
This isn't the only case.
Very little documentation.
Lo que yo quiero estar
con mi hijo.
I know that's not true.
And the shelters really don't
know what to do with them.
I just got another person
at D.H.S. to confirm this.
I have this number.
We're going to publish
the story.
I have this number.
♪
Give Extra, get extra
with new Extra Refreshers gum.
Look! Make a wish!
I wish for a Biggie
Bag from Wendy's.
I wish everyone loved each
other and was always...
That's a great wish, Jimmy.
Get a Bacon Double stack with
a quarter pound of fresh beef,
nuggets, fries and a
drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
(VO)
The ant mindlessly marches on.
Carrying up to 50 times it's
body weight.
It never questions
the tasks at hand.
But this year, there's a more
thrilling path to follow.
(Father)
Kids...
...Change of plans!
(VO)
Defy the laws of human nature...
...at the summer of Audi sales
event
Get exceptional offers now!
I can't believe it.
That I won the "Best Of"
sweepstakes
and I get to be in this GEICO
commercial?
Let's do the eyebrows first,
just tease it a little.
Slather it all over,
don't hold back.
Well, the squirrels followed me
all the way out to California!
And there's a very strange
badger staring at me...
No, I can't believe how easy it
was to save hundreds of dollars
on my car insurance with GEICO.
Uh-huh, where's the camel?
"Mr. Big Shot's" got his
own trailer.
♪ ♪
WHEEEEEEE!
Believe it!
GEICO could save you
15% or more on car insurance.
So I can buy from
Enterprise Car Sales and you'll
take ANY trade-in?
That's right!
Great!
Here you go...
Well, it does need
to be a vehicle.
But - I need this out of
my house.
(VO) With fair, transparent
value for every trade-in...
Enterprise makes it easy.
>> Announcer: "NFL LIVE" IS
BROUGHT TO YOU BY NEWT TREE
WHOLESOME ESSENTIAL PET FOODS.
NUTRO.
AND GEICO.
15 MINUTES COULD SAVE YOU 15% OR
MORE ON CAR INSURANCE.
>> DID YOU SHOWER TODAY?
>> PRESS CONFERENCE FROM OUR OWN
DAN GRAZIANO.
SOURCE AS CORDYING TO DAN CBA
COLLECTIVE BARGAINING AGREEMENTS
BETWEEN THE NFL AND PLAYERS
ASSOCIATION ARE EXPECTED TO
INTENSIFY THIS SUMMER IN AN
EFFORT TO GET A NEW DEAL DONE BY
THE START OF THE 2019 SEASON.
THREE TO FOUR NEGOTIATES
SESSIONS POSSIBLE IN THE MONTH
OF JULY ALONE.
FORMER PACKERS WIDE RECEIVER
RANDALL COBB SIGNED BY THE
COWBOYS IN FREE AGENCY TEAMED UP
WITH AARON RODGERS FOR OVER
5,000 RECEIVING YARDS AFTER
BEING DRAFTED BY THE PACK IN
2011.
HE WILL FACE HIS FORMER TEAM
WEEK FIVE IN DALLAS AND HE HAD
TO SAY THIS ABOUT MOVING ON FROM
GREEN BAY.
IT'S LIKE THE EX-GIRLFRIEND THAT
BREAK UP WITH YOU.
WHEN YOU SEE HER FIVE YEARS
LATER YOU HOPE YOU'RE IN A
BETTER SITUATION THAN YOU WERE
BEFORE.
MARRIED WITH KIDS AND ABLE TO
SAY, YEAH, I DID BETTER WITHOUT
YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT, HE'S RIGHT.
NOBODY SAYS THAT BUT THAT'S HOW
EVERYBODY FEELS.
NOT EVERY BREAKUP HAS TO BE
CONTENTIOUS.
I DON'T CARE IF IT'S THE BEST
BREAKUP EVER.
LIFE WASN'T SO GREAT --
>> YOU'RE WINNING, I'M NOT.
>> YOU WANT TO WIN.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
ANYWAY, THAT GOT US THINKING
FIVE YEARS FROM NOW WHO IS
BETTER OFF?
WE SAW A NUMBER OF NFL BREAKUPS,
IF YOU WILL SO FIVE-YEAR MARK.
RANDALL COBB OR THE GREEN BAY
PACKERS WHOCHLT IS BETTER OFF.
>> I'M GOING WITH RANDALL.
HE'S JOINING A TEAM IN THE
COWBOYS THAT'S A YOUNGER TEAM.
I THINK THEY'RE AN OVERALL
BETTER TEAM RIGHT NOW THAN THE
GREEN BAY PACKERS BUT I THINK IN
FIVE YEARS HE'LL BE IN THE
PLAYOFFS A COUPLE OF TIMES.
HE'LL -- HE'S OBVIOUS IN THE MIX
THAT HAVE WIDE RECEIVING CORE
AND THAT SLOT POSITION IS
IMPORTANT IN THE NFL NOWADAYS
AND I THINK OVERALL HE'LL JUST
BE BETTER.
DAK PRESCOTT HAS A BETTER
QUARTERBACK.
THAT WILL SERVE HIM BETTER GIVEN
THAT LONGEVITY AND BE THERE FOR
A COUPLE YEARS AND BUILD THAT
CAMARADERIE WITH DAK THAT WILL
SERVE HIM.
>> HE WON'T MISS AARON RODGERS
AT ALL.
>> THEY'RE A BETTER OVERALL
TEAM.
>> FIVE YEARS.
A LOT CAN HAPPEN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> LISTEN, THERE WERE NO -- IN
MY OPINION NO MORE NOTABLE
BREAKUP THAN THAT ONE BETWEEN
ODELL BECKHAM JR. AND THE NEW
YORK GIANTS.
THIS IS EASY IF YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT NOW.
BUT FIVE YEARS.
>> ODELL BECKHAM JR. IS GOING TO
BE IN A MUCH BETTER POSITION.
HE GOT PAID, TONS OF MONEY AND
HAS OPPORTUNITY TO MAKE MORE
MONEY.
PRICE OF LIVING IN CLEVELAND IS
LOWER.
TAKKS ARE LOWER.
SO FROM A PERSONAL FINANCIAL
STANDPOINT ODELL BECKHAM JR. IS
WINNING BIG TIME BUT WHEN IT
COMES TO FOOTBALL, THERE IS NO
QUARTERBACK THAT I BELIEVE HAS
MORE POTENTIAL TO BE ONE OF THE
GREATEST THAN I BELIEVE IN WHAT
BAKER MAYFIELD COULD DO IN TERMS
OF THE CONTINUITY AND THE TEAM
THEY'RE BUILDING COMPARED TO NEW
YORK.
WE'RE NOT SURE WHAT WILL HAPPEN
TO HAT SHURMUR IF HE WILL BE
THERE.
HE COULD BE ON THE HOT SEAT IF
IT DOESN'T WORK.
IT SEEMS CLEVELAND IS A MUCH
BETTER OFF PLACE FOR ODELL
BECKHAM JR. SO I THINK HE'S
GOING TO LOOK BACK AND GO, YOU
KNOW WHAT, THAT'S GOOD.
>> WHAT IS INTERESTING THE
GIANTS HAD A COUPLE OF BREAKUPS.
LANDON COLLINS, BETTER OFF IN
FIVE YEARS.
>> I'LL GO THE OTHER WAY.
THE NEW YORK GIANTS AND DAVE
GETTLEMAN.
WHAT WE LOOK AT WHAT DMEF'S DONE
TO REHIM THEY ACQUIRED BETHEA
AND PEPPERS THAT SENT ODELL
BECKHAM TO CLEVELAND AND
ALTHOUGH COLLINS IS A GOOD
PLAYER I THOUGHT HE WAS MORE
PRODUCTIVE CLOSER TO THE LINE OF
SCRIMMAGE.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE WAY PEPPERS
PLAYS HE CAN REPLACE HIM.
SO IT'S NOT FIVE YEARS, WE KNOW
WE'RE BETTER OFF WITHOUT LANDON.
>> WOW.
ALL RIGHT.
FAIR ENOUGH.
NOTED.
YOU KNOW, SAID THERE WAS NO
BIGGER BREAKUP THEN I THOUGHT
ABOUT A.B. AND THE STEELERS.
I WANT TO RETRACT THAT.
ANTONIO BROWN AND THE STEELERS.
THIS ONE I THINK IS TRICKY AGAIN
TALKING ABOUT FIVE SEASONS OUT.
WHO IS BETTER OFF.
>> I'M GOING WITH THE STEELERS.
I REALLY FEEL LIKE THE STEELERS
ORGANIZATION AS A WHOLE WILL BE
FULLY TURN THE PAGE FULLY FROM
ANTONIO BROWN DRAMA AND BE
LOOKING TO JUJU.
HE'LL BE TENURED, A TRUE VETERAN
LEADER ON THAT TEAM.
UNDERSTAND WHO HE IS.
BIG BEN, WHO KNOWS HOW MANY
YEARS HE HAS LEFT BUT WITH THAT
BODY FRAME HE CAN STILL BE THERE
FIVE YEARS FROM NOW PLAYING AT A
HIGH LEVEL BUT THESE GUYS ARE
READY TO PLAY AS A TEAM AS A
PERSPECTIVE ONCE THEY GET RID OF
THE DRAMA AND NEGATIVITY
SURROUND THE TEAM WITH Le'VEON
BELL AND ALL OF THESE THINGS, I
THINK FIVE YEARS FROM NOW THIS
TEAM WILL BE BETTER.
BEN ROETHLISBERGER WILL BE
RELAXED AND THE TEAM WILL BE
GOOD TO GO.
>> PERFECT SEGUE.
HOW ABOUT Le'VEON BELL AND THE
PITTSBURGH STEELERS.
>> I THINK WE SAW A LITTLE BIT
OF A PREVIEW LAST YEAR, RIGHT?
BELL WAS A STEELER BUT HE REALLY
WASN'T.
>> WASN'T.
>> SO WE'LL GO WITH THE
PITTSBURGH STEELERS AND TALKING
ABOUT JAMES CONNER WHO FILLED IN
LAST YEAR FOR Le'VEON BELL.
WE HAVE ANOTHER YEAR WITH HIM
NOW IN THE OFF-SEASON PROGRAM
AND I THINK REALLY WHERE WE'RE
GOING TO MISS BELL, GUYS, IS AS
A RUSHER BUT A RECEIVER BUT
JAMES CON CERRA A REALLY GOOD
RUNNING BACK.
PRODUCTIVE BETWEEN TACKLES AND
GOOD PASS PROTECTOR AND ANOTHER
YEAR OF GOING INTO THE JOB, I
THINK PITTSBURGH YEAR IN AND
YEAR OUT DOES A GREAT JOB OF
LETTING GUYS MOVE ON AND
REPLACING BELL AND AGREE WITH
VICTOR AND THINK THEY'LL REPLACE
A.B. AND REPLACE BELL VERY WELL
WITH JAMES CONNER.
>> ALL RIGHT, I DO THINK THAT
TEAM HAS SORT OF RALLIED AROUND
THE DEPARTURES.
THAT'S NOW.
WE'LL SEE WHERE THEY ARE IN A
FEW SEASONS.
THIS LAST ONE, I'M NOT SURE THEY
DATED.
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY WENT OUT.
>> IT WAS A HOOKUP.
THE CARDINALS AND --
>> I THINK JOSH ROSEN WILL BE
BETTER OFF.
HE HAD THE WEIGHT OF THE WORLD
ON HIS SHOULDERS.
HE WAS A TOP DRAFT PICK.
THE ANSWER TO THE ARIZONA
CARDINALS ORGANIZATION.
OF COURSE THAT DIDN'T WORK OUT
SO HERE HE IS IN MIAMI NOW, THE
PRESSURE IS REALLY OFF.
HE'S GOT A NEW HEAD COACH HERE.
THEY'RE GOING TO BE RUNNING A
NEW ENGLAND SYSTEM.
BY THE WAY IF YOU RUN THE NEW
ENGLAND OFFENSIVE SYSTEM YOU GOT
TO BE A SMART GUY.
THAT'S WHAT JOSH ROSEN IS.
ELSE'S A SMART GUY AND I THINK
HE'S GOING TO FIT IN WELL THERE
AND IS GOING TO BE A PLACE --
OH, BY THE WAY HE HAS
FITZPATRICK BEHIND HIM THAT
DOESN'T HAVE THE ATTITUDE OF A
START THEIR DOESN'T WANT TO
HELP.
TWO SMART GUYS IN THE
QUARTERBACK ROOM, A MUCH BETTER
PLACE FOR JOSH.
>> DIANNA, WHAT ABOUT KYLER
MURRAY?
YOU DON'T THINK THEY HAVE A
CHANCE TO BE A DYNAMIC
PLAYMAKER --
>> THAT'S WHAT THE QUESTION IS.
AN ASSESSMENT OF KYLER MURRAY IN
A LOT OF WAYS.
THE BIG QUESTION MARK WILL IT
WORK?
TO ME MY BIGGEST ISSUE WITH
ARIZONA IS LAST YEAR AND THIS
YEAR IS THEIR OFFENSIVE LINE SO
AS MUCH AS WE CAN SAY KYLER
MURRAY.
>> I GOT FIVE YEARS --
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> LOOKING FOR A GM.
>> NO.
TRYING TO GET RID OF ME?
I GOT FIVE YEAR.
>> BREAKING UP IS HARD TO DO.
>> YOU GAVE ME FIVE YEARS.
>> I DID.
>> FAIR ENOUGH.
ALL RIGHT.
WHEN WE COME BACK, JUJU
SMITH-SCHUSTER ISN'T THINKING
FIVE YEARS.
HE'S THINKING RIGHT NOW AND
WE'LL TALK ROLE MODELS AND
STEELERS CULTURE COMING UP.
>> HI, I'M JUJU SMITH-SCHUSTER
AND WANT TO TELL YOU HOW MUCH
FUN I'M HAVING THIS OFF-SEASON.
(Client's Voice)
Remember that degree
you got in taxation?
(Danny)
Of course you don't
because you didn't!
Your job isn't
understanding tax code...
it's understanding why that...
will get him a body like that...
MOVE!
...that.
Your job isn't
doing hard work...
Here.
...it's making
her do hard work...
...and getting paid for it.
(VO)
Snap and sort your expenses to
save over $4,600 at tax time.
(Danny)
Jody...
...it's time to get yours!
(VO)
QUICKBOOKS. BACKING YOU.
♪ Hello? ♪
Flamin' Hot
Nacho?
They made the original hot
(hot hot)?
♪♪
♪ Hello? ♪
♪ Here's a shake up ♪
♪ My Hot Flamin's mixin'
with Doritos ♪
♪ Why all these people
in my face ♪
♪ Wanna be my Ace ♪
♪ Wanna be my Migo ♪
♪ Talkin' bout how far
back we go ♪
♪ Way way way way back ♪
♪ I don't care about that ♪
♪ I ain't sharin' my snacks ♪
I made this for you.
Wonderful.
♪ Hello? ♪
Now It's Hot
How do you gauge the
greatness of an SUV?
Is it to carry cargo
or to carry on a legacy?
Its show of strength
or its sign of intelligence?
In crossing harsh terrain
or breaking new ground?
This is the time to get
an exceptional offer
on the Mercedes of
your midsummer dreams
at the Mercedes-Benz Summer
Event, going on now.
Lease the GLA 250 SUV
for just $329 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz
Summer Event.
Mercedes-Benz.
The best or nothing.
>>> GO LONG, PAL.
♪♪♪
>> IS THIS WHERE THE IMMACULATE
FOOTBALL WAS?
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> WHENEVER I SAY WE'RE GOING TO
WIN THE GAME I GUARANTEE IT.
>> I MEANT IT.
>> STARTED THE NFL.
WHOA.
>> QUIT LOOKING AT MY CHEST
HAIR.
LOOK AT THE PLAY.
>> GET THOSE LEGS UP.
>> THAT IS JUJU SMITH-SCHUSTER.
SMITH-SCHUSTER PAST MIDFIELD.
>> EXTRA POINT.
>> BY THE MAN CALLED JUJU.
JUJU, JUJU SMITH-SCHUSTER IN THE
BACK OF THE END ZONE.
WOW.
>> WE'RE JOINED THIS AFTERNOON
BY JUJU SMITH-SCHUSTER WHO IS
MAKING HIS WAY ALL THE WAY
ACROSS THE ATLANTIC.
HE IS IN LONDON THIS AFTERNOON
FOR THE NFL ACADEMY WHERE HE'S
AN AMBASSADOR.
JUJU, TELL US EXACTLY WHAT THAT
IS AND WHAT IT MEANS THERE IN
LONDON.
>> SO, HERE IN LONDON WE'RE
WORKING WITH THE NFL ACADEMY
WHICH IS AN AMAZING THING.
THEY GIVE THE OPPORTUNITY TO
PLAYERS, YOUNG PLAYERS FROM THE
AGE OF 15 AND UP, YOU KNOW, WHO
LEARN THE NEW GAME, AMERICAN
FOOTBALL.
THIS IS NEW TO THEM WHICH IS
AWESOME BUT IT'S AWESOME BECAUSE
IT JUST GIVES THEM THE
OPPORTUNITY TO HAVE ANOTHER
CAREER, ANOTHER WAY TO PLAY IN
THE STATES IN THE NFL.
>> WE TALKED TO JAMES CONNER
YESTERDAY.
HE TALKED ABOUT TURNING THE
PAGE.
ABOUT THE CHANGES THAT HAD GONE
ON IN PITTSBURGH DURING THE
OFF-SEASON.
WHAT IS THE TEMPERATURE OF THIS
TEAM AS YOU GET READY FOR
TRAINING CAMP?
>> WE'RE NOT TOO COLD.
WE'RE NOT TOO HOT.
THE WEATHER IS NICE.
EVERYONE IS ON THE SAME PAGE.
FOCUS ON THE SAME GOAL WHICH IS
AMAZING BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE ALL ABOUT.
ABOUT THE TEAM.
THERE'S NO INDIVIDUALS AND HERE
TO WIN GAMES.
>> JUJU, TALK TO ME ABOUT SOME
OF THE TALENT YOU'RE SEEING IN
LONDON.
ANY BALLERS OUT THERE?
ANY FUTURE STEELERS OUT THIS OR
WHAT?
>> MAN, THERE'S SOME TALENT
HERE.
THERE'S SOME POTENTIAL.
I MEAN YOU GOT TO UNDERSTAND
THIS GAME IS NEW TO THEM.
WE STARTED LIFTING WEIGHTS AT
14.
THEY'RE BARELY STARTING AT 16,
17.
IF WE'RE TO GET THEM ON THE
RIGHT PAGE IT WOULD BE AMAZING
TO START A POP CARNER AND START
IN MIDDLE SCHOOL, HIGH SCHOOL
AND THAT WOULD BE THEIR ACADEMY.
>> ALL RIGHT, JUJU, IT'S BEEN
WELL DOCUMENTED THAT ANTONIO
BROWN IS NO LONGER WITH THE
STEELERS.
NOW YOU'RE THE NUMBER ONE GUY.
HOW DOES IT FEEL?
DO YOU FEEL A DIFFERENCE IN THE
LOCKER ROOM?
ARE PEOPLE TREATING YOU
DIFFERENTLY?
ARE DUDES GETTING YOUR TRAYS OF
LUNCH FOR YOU?
IS IT A DIFFERENT FEELING BEING
THE NUMBER ONE GUY?
HOW DOES IT FEEL?
>> NO, MAN, IT FEELS NO
DIFFERENT.
I MEAN ALWAYS PEOPLE SAY, OH,
YOU'RE THE NUMBER ONE GUY THIS
YEAR BUT MORE FOR MYSELF I GIVE
MYSELF MORE OPPORTUNITY FOR
OTHERS GUY TO STEP UP.
TALK ABOUT A.B. HAVING A HUNDRED
CATCHES OVER A THOUSAND YARDS.
THOSE WILL BE SPREAD OUT BETWEEN
JAMES CONNER, JAMES WASHINGTON,
DONTE MONCRIEF, JAMES SAMUELS.
SO MANY GUYS WILL GET MORE
TOUCHES, MORE CATCHES, MORE YAC.
I'M THE STILL SAME GUY IN THE
LOCKER ROOM.
>> THE 22-YEAR-OLD VERSION OF
JUJU SMITH-SCHUSTER AND, JUJU,
YOU REFERENCED THE FOOTBALL
BEING SPREAD AROUND.
THAT MAKES THE COMMUNICATION
WITH BEN ROETHLISBERGER ALL THAT
MORE IMPORTANT.
WHAT IS YOUR RELATIONSHIP LIKE
WITH YOUR QUARTERBACK?
>> IT'S AMAZING, MAN.
BEN, HE'S A GREAT LEADER.
GREAT DUDE.
HE TOOK THE WHOLE OFFENSIVE
GROUP DOWN TO HIS HOUSE IN
GEORGIA.
AMAZING, YOU KNOW, WE SPEND TIME
TOGETHER.
BONDING, WORKED HARD.
THREW.
AT THE END OF THE DAY IT'S LIKE
DURING THAT BONDING THAT
CONNECTION AND WHAT HE DID FOR
US WAS AMAZING.
I THINK IT'S SO CRAZY THAT A GUY
WHO HAS BEEN IN THE LEAGUE FOR
15, 16 YEARS SEES SO MANY GUYS
COME AND GO AND, YOU KNOW, FOR
ME I'M ONLY 22 YEARS OLD.
I MET HIM I WAS 20 YEARS OLD AND
OUR BOND IS JUST -- WE'RE JUST
GOING TO KEEP GROWING.
>> AS AN ATHLETE, AS THE
SUPERSTAR ATHLETE YOU ARE,
YOU'RE ALWAYS WORKING ON
SOMETHING NEW.
GIVE ME ONE THING YOU'VE BEEN
WORKING ON TO EITHER GET BETTER
AT OR SOMETHING YOU WANT TO ADD
TO YOUR GAME OR WHATEVER THE
CASE MAY BE?
>> MAN, I WANT TO REALLY, REALLY
FOCUS AND PLAY MORE INSIDE AND
OUTSIDE LEARNING THE WHOLE
PACKAGE, LEARNING THE WHOLE
OFFENSE.
THAT'S WHAT SPATES BEING ON THE
FIELD THE WHOLE GAME AND BEING
ON THE FIELD CERTAIN PLAY,
CERTAIN PACKAGES.
I THINK IT'S GREAT I'M ABLE TO
PLAY OUTSIDE, INSIDE, RIGHT
SIDE, LEFT SIDE.
YOU KNOW, MOVEMENT AND IT'S THE
SAME, THAT WILL HELP OUT A LOT
AND THAT'S SOMETHING I'VE BEEN
FOCUSED ON STUDYING THAT
PLAYBOOK AND UNDERSTANDING WHAT
EVERYBODY HAS TO DO.
>> JUJU, WE ALSO GET TO SEE
EVERYTHING ELSE YOU DO VIA
SOCIAL MEDIA.
DOES ANYBODY IN THE NFL HAVE
MORE FUN THAN YOU DO?
>> NOT NECESSARILY.
I MEAN I DO A LOT OF STUFF ON
YOUTUBE SO A LOT OF STUFF I DO
ON THAT END.
I REALLY LOVE TO SHOW MY
PERSONAL SIDE ON MY FUN SIDE
WHAT I DO IN MY FREE TIME
PLAYING AND MAKING YOUTUBE
VIDEOS.
I THINK A LOT OF GUYS IN THE NFL
JUST POST A LOT OF WORKING OUT
WHICH IS NOTHING WRONG WITH
THAT, YOU KNOW, BUT WHAT DO THEY
LIKE TO DO IN THEIR FREE TIME?
DO THEY LIKE TO TRAVEL THE
WORLD, STAY HOME AND WATCH
MOVIES.
I THINK A LOT OF THEIR FANS
WOULD LIKE THAT.
>> SOME LIKE TO GO TO PROM WHICH
APPARENTLY YOU DID RECENTLY.
TELL US ABOUT THE PROM.
>> SO THE PROM WAS AWESOME.
YOU KNOW, A KID, HE'S FROM P.A.,
PITTSBURGH.
IDEALLY HE WANTED TO TAKE THIS
GIRL THAT HE LIKED A LOT AND HIS
BEST FRIEND ENDS UP TAKING HER.
HE TOLD HIS BEST FRIEND BUT HIS
BEST FRIEND WENT BEHIND HIS GIRL
AND TOOK THIS GIRL SO HE ASKED
ME, MAN, LET'S ONE-UP BUY A
SUIT, GET A PARTY BUS.
WE BASICALLY STOLE THE NIGHT
AWAY FOR HIM AND AT THE END OF
THE DAY I MET THE GUY.
HE SEEMS LIKE A GOOD KID SO HE'S
GREAT.
MY FRIEND IS GREAT BECAUSE HE
GOT LIKE 20K FOLLOWERS, ANTHONY
SO HE'S SUPER EXCITED ABOUT HIS
COLLEGE CAREER COMING SOON.
>> ANTHONY ONE FRIEND AND
GIRLFRIEND NOTHING.
HE WINS.
>> JUJU, WE SAW YOU GETTING BUSY
ON THE DANCE FLOOR RIGHT THERE.
TALK TO ME ABOUT WHAT
CELEBRATIONS YOU GOT IN STORE.
I KNOW YOU'RE ALWAYS CREATIVE
AND BRING NEW STUFF TO THE
TABLE.
WHAT YOU GOT IN STORE FOR US
THIS YEAR FROM THE CELEBRATION
STANDPOINT?
>> MAN, DON'T LOOK.
I'M SO EXCITED.
YES, I'M THE YOUNG DUDE IN THE
ROOM BUT I'M VOCAL.
IT'S MY TIME TO STEP UP AND BE A
LEADER AND GETTING EVERYBODY ON
THE PAGE TO DO A CELEBRATION.
DONTE MONCRIEF IS OLDER BUT ALL
THESE GUYS, MY RECEIVERS, JAMES
WASHINGTON IS ON THE SAME PAGE
BECAUSE WE'RE IN THE SAME CLASS
AND THEN I'M STILL WORKING ON
BIG BEN, YOU KNOW AND THE
O-LINEMEN.
THEY ARE A LOT OLDER SO THEY'RE
VETS.
BEEN HERE BEFORE.
WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
MAJOR CELEBRATION COMING SOON.
>> WE CAN'T WAIT.
LAST QUESTION WE ASKED JAMES
CONNER THIS YESTERDAY TO CLOSE
THINGS OUT.
WHY SHOULD STEELER FANS BE
OPTIMISTIC AS WE LOOK TOWARDS
2019?
>> MAN, YOU KNOW, STEELER FANS
ARE ALWAYS SUPPORTING US SINCE
DAY ONE WHETHER WE DO BAD OR
GOOD.
I DON'T DOUBT THEY'LL SUPPORT US
TO THE END.
I'M KIND OF HAPPY LIKE WHERE
WE'RE AT RIGHT NOW WE'RE NOT
LIKE THE HEADLINE, THE BROWNS,
THEY'RE THE TEAM THAT EVERYONE
IS WATCHING WHAT KIND OF NOISE
THEY'LL MAKE.
I'M SUPER EXCITED TO WATCH THEM
PLAY TOO.
SEEING OBJ COMMENTING ON MY POST
AND I'M COMMENTING ON HIS POST.
CAN'T WAIT.
THE FANS WILL SUPPORT UNTIL THE
END BECAUSE WE'LL FINISH STRONG
AND ALWAYS FOE THAT.
>> BEST OF LUCK.
WE APPRECIATE YOU BEING WITH US.
>> THANKS FOR BEING WITH US, JU.
>> THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE IT.
>> WITH ANTONIO BROWN NOW
DEPARTED TO OAKLAND, JUJU WILL
BECOME BIG BEN'S NUMBER ONE MAN
AND HE SHOULD RECEIVE TIGHTER
COVERAGE.
OVER THE LAST TWO SEASONS WHEN
FACING PRESS COVERAGE JUJU
ACTUALLY HAD A BETTER PASS RATE
AND YARDS PER TARGET THAN
ANTONIO BROWN.
CLEARLY, VICTOR, PERSPECTIVE
CHANGES A LITTLE BIT, I WILL
THINK.
HE'S THE NUMBER ONE GUY.
HE CAN SAY WHATEVER.
YOU KNOW, WHAT KIND OF PRESSURE?
HOW IS IT DIFFERENT FOR JUJU
STARTING THIS SEASON TAN SAY
LAST YEAR.
>> THE ONLY THING DIFFERENT IS
THE MIND-SET, PERSPECTIVE.
COMING INTO THAT LOCKER ROOM AND
ANTONIO BROWN IS NOT THERE.
JUST YOU AND NOW YOU BECOME KIND
OF THAT LEADER.
PEOPLE ARE LOOKING TO YOU.
YOU'VE BEEN THERE.
YOU UNDERSTAND WHO YOU ARE.
22 YEARS OLD BUT NOW YOU BECOME
THE GUY THAT THE YOUNGER PEOPLE,
THE YOUNGER TEAMMATES ARE
LOOKING UP TO YOU WANTING TO
KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING AND WANT
TOCK HANG OUT WITH YOU IN THE
OFF-SEASON AND STEAL A LITTLE
KNOWLEDGE FROM YOU AND YOUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH BEN AND GET A
HEAD START ON WHAT THEY NEED TO
DO TO GET BETTER AND HE LEADS
THE CHARGE IN THAT REGARD AND
IT'S PRETTY BIG SHOES TO FILL.
>> I THINK THE STEELERS HAVE
DONE A GREAT JOB AND WERE
PREPARING FOR THIS FOR A NUMBER
OF YEARS AND THERE WAS THAT
WHOLE NOTION OF WE HAVE TO BIN
FOR TODAY AND DEVELOP FOR
TOMORROW.
AND YOU LOOK AT THAT POSITION
AND THAT ORGANIZATION GOING BACK
TO MIKE WALLACE, SANTONIO
HOLMES, OBVIOUSLY ANTONIO BROWN,
SMITH-SCHUSTER, DO A GREAT JOB
OF GETTING GUYS IN THE PIPELINE
AND DEVELOPED AND NOW ANTONIO
BROWN MOVES ON, SMITH-SCHUSTER
STEPS UP AND HAVE DONE A
REMARKLY GREAT JOB FOR A NUMBER
OF YEARS AT THIS POSITION.
>> I THINK THAT'S A GAIT POINT
AND WOULD ARGUE OUTSIDE OF NEW
ENGLAND THEY POSSIBLY DO IT AS
WELL AS ANYBODY IN TERMS OF
CONTINUITY AND NOW ANTONIO BROWN
ENDED IN A WAY THEY PROBABLY
DIDN'T ANTICIPATE BUT DID
ANTICIPATE IT WOULD END AT SOME
POINT AND TO YOUR POINT THEY
SEEM TO BE SORT OF IN LOCKSTEP
WITH PLANNING FOR THE FUTURE.
>> I THINK THERE'S THREE THINGS
THAT JUJU JOOUMG HAS TO PROBABLY
FOCUS ON THIS SEASON.
IT'S GOING FROM BEING A GREAT
RECEIVER TO AN ELITE RECEIVER.
HE NEEDS TO PLAY AT THAT LEVEL.
VICTOR TOUCHED ON THE LEADERSHIP
ASPECT.
OBVIOUSLY JUST FROM THAT
INTERVIEW YOU CAN HEAR HE HAS
STEPPED UP TO BE THE LEAD EVER
TALKING ABOUT TRYING TO GET BIG
BEN AND THE OFFENSIVE LINE TO
PARTICIPATE IN HIS CELEBRATION
DRILLS AND THEY OBVIOUSLY HAVE
GOOD CHEMISTRY THERE AND THEN
THAT THIRD LAYER IS BEING A
MENTOR TO THOSE YOUNGER GUYS SO
HE'S GOING TO BE ASKED A LOT
MORE OF HIM AS A FOOTBALL PLAYER
OUT ON THE FIELD AND OF COURSE
IN THE LOCKER ROOM BUT IF
THERE'S ONE THING I THINK WE'VE
LEARNED ABOUT JUJU OVER THE
YEARS IS HE ATTACKS EVERYTHING
WITH OPEN ARMS.
HE IS AN OPEN BOOK HIMSELF.
HE EMBRACES THAT ROLE AND HE
WANTS TO BE THAT CHARACTER GUY.
HE WANTS TO BE THAT GOOD GUY AND
WHEN HE TAOS TO PLAYERS ON THE
STEELERS ABOUT JUJU SMITH AND
WHAT HIS PERSONALITY IS LIKE
OBVIOUSLY ON SOCIAL MEDIA HE'S
SO MUCH FUN, APPARENTLY HE DOES
A LOT OF HIS WORK SILENTLY.
HE'S NOT THE LOUDEST GUY IN THE
ROOM.
NOT THE ONE JOKING AROUND DURING
DRILLS.
HE LIKES TO HAVE FUN BUT HE IS
LOCKED IN AND FOCUSED AND I
THINK IF HE CAN TAKE HIT GAME TO
THAT'S LET LEVEL THE ANTONIO
BROWN CONVERSATIONS THAT WE'RE
GOING TO BE HAVING WILL FEEL SO
LONG AGO.
>> HE SAID THAT WAS REALLY
IMPRESSIVE IN THE INTERVIEW AND
TOUCHED ON THE END ABOUT THE
STEELERS ARE ALWAYS THERE IN THE
EN.
IT'S NOT WHERE YOU START.
IT'S WHERE YOU END AND YOU LOOK
AT PITTSBURGH AND NEW ENGLAND.
THOSE TEAM ALWAYS IMPROVE DURING
THE COURSE OF THE SEASON SO
JAMES CONNER, SMITH-SCHUSTER IN
A NEW ROLE.
NOT WHAT THEY LOOK LIKE IN
AUGUST OR SEPTEMBER.
ARE THEY ASCENDING AND GETTING
BETTER AND MIKE TOMLIN DESERVES
SO MUCH CREDIT.
PLAYER DEVELOPMENT.
THE WAY THEY COACH THEIR PLAYERS
GET BETTER AND I THOUGHT HIS
POINT WAS A GOOD ONE WHICH IS,
HEY, WE'LL BE THERE IN THE END
BECAUSE THAT'S WHERE THEY'VE
BEEN YEAR IN AND YEAR OUT.
>> SEEMS LIKE THEY TRANSFORM AND
MORPH INTO WHATEVER THEY NEED TO
BE TO WIN TOWARD THE SECOND HALF
OF 9 SEASON AND KEEPS THEM IN
THE HUNT.
>> FROM ALL KIND OF REASONS WHY
EVERYBODY IS LOOKING TO
CLEVELAND BUT I THINK YOU'D BE
UNWISE TO SLEEP ON PITTSBURGH IN
ANY WAY SHAPE OR FORM.
MIKE TOMLIN, A VETERAN SQUAD, A
GOOD TEAM.
I THINK YOU COULD ARGUE
UNDERACHIEVED LAST SEASON.
WE'LL SEE.
WHAT DO PATRICK MAHOMES, SAQUON
BARKLEY AND KYLER MURRAY HAVE IN
COMMON?
THEY TURN HEADS.
WE'LL CROWN THE HIGHLIGHT KING
NEXT.
>> YOU EVER WATCH HIGHLIGHTS
FROM YOUTUBE?
>> PATRICK MAHOMES ON FIRE.
>> ONE WAY, ZINGS IT ANOTHER.
>> GIANTS OVER THE TOP.
>> TOUCHDOWNS KYLER MURRAY.
AN ABSOLUTE DIME.
>> HE'S THE BEST QUARTERBACK
YOU'LL EVER SEE AT EVERYTHING
ELSE EXCEPT HEIGHT.
>> PATRICK MAHOMES WITH MAHOMES
MAGIC.
If only there was a place nearby
>>you could get one of these.
Or these.
Good thing they're
sold literally
everywhere business is done.
I'm pretty sure you could
buy them at a bank.
Not Sorry.
Reese's.
Too many people
in pain settle for
Not Sorry.
a restless night's sleep.
There's a better choice.
Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid
and the 12-hour
pain-relieving
strength of Aleve.
That dares to last
into the morning.
So you feel refreshed.
ALEVE PM.
There's a better choice.
What does it take to
burn one calorie
and enjoy the great
taste of Miller Lite?
A walk to the bar.
More Taste Is Worth
One More Calorie.
What are you holding?
Miller Lite. Hold True.
♪ ♪ ♪
Start the car! Start the car!
The IKEA Summer Sale.
Wooooooo!
Save up to 50% off select
items in store only
June 26th to July 7th.
IKEA.
>>> WITH THE FIRST PICK THE NEW
ORLEANS PELICANS PICK ZION
WILLIAMSON.
THE NEW YORK KNICKS SELECT R.J.
BERRY.
>> MY DREAM CAME TRUE.
I'M JUST READY TO WORK.
>> NBA SUMMER LEAGUE ACTION ON
FRIDAY.
IT'S TRIPLE HEADER STARTING AT
7:30 EASTERN ON ESPN.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS A SPECIAL
MATCH-UP AT 9:30 FEATURING
FORMER DUKE TEAMMATE ZION AND
R.J. BARRETT FACING OFF FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN THE ASSOCIATION.
JOSINA ANDERSON UPDATES.
CBA NEGOTIATING SESSIONS FOR
JULY 17th THROUGH THE 19th.
THERE WILL BE THE FIRST TIME
BOTH SIDES ENGAGE IN TALKS FOR
THREE CONSECUTIVE DAYS
SPECIFICALLY ON THIS PENDING
LEAGUE DEAL.
DAN GRAZIANO REPORTING THERE IS
HOPE OF GETTING A NEW CBA BY THE
START OF THE 2019 SEASON.
>> GREAT.
>> LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT A FEW
NFL PLAYERS NOMINATED FOR THE
ESPYS.
AFTER AN IMPRESSIVE SOPHOMORE
SEASON THROWING OVER 5,000 YARDS
AND WON AN MVP JUST THAT,
PATRICK MAHOMES NOMINATED FOR
BEST MALE ATHLETE.
SAQUON BARKLEY NOMINATE THE FOR
THE BEST BREAKTHROUGH ATHLETE
LAST SEASON, BARKLEY RUSHED FOR
1307 YARDS.
BROKE A GIANTS ROOKIE RECORD.
KYLER MURRAY BECAME THE SEVENTH
PLAYER TO WIN THE HEISMAN IN
OU'S HISTORY.
NONE OF THOSE ARE TOO SHABBY.
TODAY WE GIVE OUT THE HIGHLIGHT
KING AWARD.
>> AN ESPY.
>> IT IS NOT?
IT SHOULD BE.
>> FUNNY, MY CHOICE HERE IS
KANSAS CITY QUARTERBACK PATRICK
MAHOMES.
HE IS UP FOR MALE ATHLETE OF THE
YEAR.
>> GETS MY VOTE.
HEARD WHY.
AGAINST THE RAVENS FACING FOURTH
AND NINE FROM THE TEAM'S 40.
MAHOMES IS HIT.
WE HAVE SEEN HIM DO COUNTLESS
TIMES WHICH WAS BUY TIME WITH
HIS FEET.
GET OUT OF BOUNDS RELIES ON HIS
RIGHT HAND.
FINES TYREEK HILL DOWNFIELD AND
AFTER THE PART ANDY REID SAID
THAT'S HOW WE DESIGN I HAD IT.
OH, SURE, ANDY.
AGAINST THE BRONCOS.
WE KNEW HIS RIGHT HAND WAS
MAGICAL.
>> DID YOU JUST SAY LUCKY.
WE NEW HIS RIGHT HAND WAS
MAGICAL.
HIS LEFT HAND HERE, SPOTS VON
MILLER COMING RIGHT AT HIM.
EVEN WHEN YOUR DEFENSE IS DOING
EVERYTHING THEY SHOULD BE DOING,
THERE ARE SITUATIONS WHERE YOU
CANNOT BE PATRICK MAHOMES
BECAUSE HE COMES UP WITH SOME
UNTHINKABLE MOMENT HERE.
HIS ATHLETICISM.
VISION OF THE FIELD AND HIS
ABILITY TO STAY IN THE POCKET
MAKE PLAYS AND OUTSIDE THE
POCKET IS WHERE HE'S PERHAPS
PROBABLY MOST DANGEROUS.
YOUR HIGHLIGHT.
OH, WAIT.
HE'S YOUR HIGHLIGHT KING.
>> HE IS MY HIGHLIGHT KING
BECAUSE HE IS A HIGHLIGHT
MACHINE.
AS YOU CAN SEE, HE'S BROKEN AT
LEAST 47 TACKLES ON THAT ONE TO
GET TO THE END ZONE.
HE'S JUST PUTTING HIS FOOT IN
THE GROUND.
WILL NOT BE DENIED AGAINST
PHILADELPHIA.
OBVIOUSLY A RIVALRY IN THAT
DIVISION AND HE'S TAKING OFF ON
THAT ONE.
IN THIS ONE, THIS ONE IS -- THIS
ONE IS PRETTY GOOD.
OKAY.
WE KNOW THIS GUY GETS A
TREMENDOUS BLOCK BY 73.
THIS RUN IS JUST INDICATIVE OF
THE TYPE OF ATHLETE THAT SAQUON
BARKLEY IS.
HE CAN SHAKE GUYS BEHIND HIM.
>>> IN FRONT OF HIM AND HAS THE
SPEED TO OUTRUN ANYONE IN THE
LEAGUE.
THAT'S WHAT WE SEE HERE AND
ALWAYS ON DISPLAY.
A BONUS, DIANNA, WHEN I HEAR
THIS ONE, HURDLE.
NOT ONLY A HANDFUL OF GUYS THAT
CAN PROBABLY COUNT THEM ON ONE
HAND WHO CAN HURTLE GUYS LIKE
THAT AND KEEP IT MOVING.
>> YOU.
YOU TALK ABOUT THAT PLAY.
>> EXACTLY.
>> PILE ON YOUR GIANTS BUT THE
FACT HE WAS ABLE TO DO THAT WITH
THAT O-LINE.
MIKE TANNENBAUM.
>> I GOT KYLER MURRAY.
I WAS AT THIS GAME.
HIS RESILIENCY WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
THEY GOT OUTPLAYED BADLY IN THE
FIRST HALF.
COMES OUT IN THE SECOND HALF.
HE STEPS UP OUT OF THE POCKET.
KEEPS HIS EYES DOWNING THE FEEL.
PUTS SO MUCH PRESSURE ON A
DEFENSE.
THROWS A REALLY ACCURATE PASS.
THIS WAS A GREAT PLAY.
GOT OKLAHOMA BACK IN THE GAME.
THIS WAS ANOTHER GAME I WAS AT.
WEST VIRGINIA'S DEFENSE WAS
HORRIFIC IN THIS GAME.
IF THEY WERE PLAYING FLAG
FOOTBALL, KYLER MURRAY STILL
WOULD HAVE GOT UNTOUCHED AND --
>> FLAG FOOTBALL.
>> YEAH.
>> THIS WAS WHAT ARIZONA WAS
HOPING FOR.
LOOK AT HOW MANY GUYS HE CAN
MAKE MISS IN SPACE AND HAVE THE
SPEED TO TAKE IT ALL THE WAY.
THE AMOUNT OF PRESSURE HE'LL PUT
ON DEMPS WILL BE FORMIDABLE IN
THE FALL BECAUSE IT WILL BE HIS
ARM AND SPEED.
LOOK AT THIS ONE.
OKLAHOMA STATE, BIG RIVALRY
GAME.
AGAIN, 50 YARDS DOWN THE FIELD.
HOLLYWOOD BROWN IN STRIDE.
THIS GUY WILL BE A DYNAMIC
PLAYMAKER.
HE IS A HIGHLIGHT MUNGONGO, THE
HIGHLIGHT TEAMMAKER AND ARIZONA
CARDINAL FANS IS WHAT THEY'RE
LOOKING FORWARD TO IN THE FALL.
>> HOPING.
WE TOLD YOU WE'D LET YOU VOTE.
NARROWED THE FIELD.
ONE OF THESE THREE HIGHLIGHT
KING SO GO TO OUR TWITTER HANDLE
@ESPNNFL AND VOTE FOR ONE OF
THESE THREE AND WE'LL LET YOU
KNOW WHAT YOU THINK.
ALSO, WHILE YOU'RE AT IT, DON'T
FORGET.
YOU CAN VOTE ON THE ESPYS RIGHT
NOW.
THAT IS @ESPYS.COM.
ROB MENDEZ.
A MAN BORN WITHOUT ARMS AND LEGS
FOUND HIS CALLING COACHING HIGH
SCHOOL FOOTBALL.
>> COMES OUT FULL HEAD OF HAIR
PARTED DOWN THE SIDE.
I TOLD HIM THERE'S NOTHING UGLY
ABOUT HIM.
HE'S STILL AN ANGEL.
(VO)
Why use Post-it Extreme Notes?
Because they make your message
stick,
getting it said, and done right,
the first time.
(Man off screen)
Aw, C'mon!
(VO)
Stop the Re-work with Post-it
Extreme Notes.
Uh-oh, looks like someone's
still nervous about buying
a new house.
Is it that obvious?
Yes it is.
You know, maybe you'd worry less
if you got GEICO to help with
your homeowners insurance.
I didn't know GEICO could helps
with homeowners insurance.
Yep,
they've been doing it for years.
What are you doing?
Big Steve?
Thanks, man.
There he is.
Get to know GEICO and see
how much you could save on
homeowners and
renters insurance.
>>> THE ESPYS AUCTION IS WHERE
CAN YOU BID ONN ONCE IF A A
LIFETIME EXPERERIENCES LIKE
JOINING ME ON THE SET OF
"SPORTSCENTER."
JOIN ME AND SUNDAY NIGHT
BASEBALL IN THE BOOTH.
>> JOIN ME AND WE'LL MAKE THE
PUPPET IN YOUR LIKENESS.
>> COME HANG OUT WITH ME AND MY
LEAST FAVORITE SON ON SOUTH
BEACH.
>> BID NOW ON EBAY.COM/ESPN.
>>> THE ESPYS AUCTION INCLUDES
AMAZING EXPERIENCES ACROSS
SPORTS AND INTERTAINMENT
INCLUDING THOSE YOU JUST HEARD
ABOUT.
GO TO EBAY.COM/ESPN TO BID NOW
THROUGH JULY 10th.
>>> WE'VE BEEN HIGHLIGHTING OUR
ESPY NOMINEES THROUGHOUT THE
SHOW BUT THIS GOES BEYOND
FOOTBALL.
HIGH SCHOOL FOOTBALL COACH ROB
MENDEZ WHO WILL BE THE RECIPIENT
OF THE JIMMY V AWARD FOR
PERSEVERANCE.
BORN WITH AN EXTREMELY RARE
CONDITION THAT AFFECTS BLESS
THAN 100 PEOPLE IN THE WORLD,
MENDEZ FOUND HIS CALLING
COACHING A SPORT HE WAS NEVER
ABLE TO PLAY HIMSELF.
FEATURED CHRONICLED AND HIS
FIRST SEASON AS A HEAD FOOTBALL
COACH CAPTURING THE INSPIRING
AND UNLIKELY STORY OF A COACH
WHO TRANSFORMED A GROUP OF YOUNG
ATHLETES FROM SKEPTICS INTO
BELIEVERS.
♪♪
>>> AT THIS TIME I JUST WANT TO
INTRODUCE TO YOU SOMEBODY I
THINK CAN REALLY HELP TURN THIS
PROGRAM AROUND.
A COACH THAT I HIRED BECAUSE I
WAS IMPRESSED WITH HIS KNOWLEDGE
OF THE GAME.
HIS PASSION BLEW ME AWAY.
EVERYTHING ELSE THAT'S ON TOP OF
THAT IN TERMS OF WHO HE IS AND
WHAT HE DOES ON A DAY-TO-DAY
BASIS INSPIRES ME.
YOUR NEW COACH, ROB MENDEZ.
[ APPLAUSE ]
♪♪
>> IT WAS AWFUL.
IT WAS REALLY, REALLY AWFUL.
I HAD TO KEEP ROBERT.
>> IN THE BACK OF MY MIND ASKING
WHY, WHY MY SON?
YOU KNOW, LESS THAN 100 BORN
LIKE HIM IN THE WORLD.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DID WITH THIS
BOY?
>> IT WAS HARD TO SEE HIM.
I REALLY DIDN'T WANT TO SEE
ROBERT.
I DIDN'T SEE ROBERT FOR ABOUT
TWO WEEKS BECAUSE I JUST -- I
DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> I JUST REMEMBER STARING, YOU
KNOW, THERE WAS A LOT OF
STARING.
LIKE HE WAS NOT A HUMAN OR
SOMETHING.
>> BUT HE'S DIFFERENT.
>> YEAH.
>> HE SEES PEOPLE'S STARING AS
AN OPPORTUNITY.
>> EVERYONE OUT THERE, YOU KNOW
ME, ROBERT MENDEZ.
>> THINGS THAT YOU AND I GET TO
DO IN TEN MINUTES MIGHT TAKE HIM
AN HOUR BUT HE NEVER COMPLAINED
ABOUT IT.
>> ROBERT WAS JUST A REALLY EASY
CHILD.
AND HE JUST WAS REALLY, REALLY
HAPPY.
>> WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE TEAM?
>> SAN FRANCISCO 49ers.
>> HAS A GIFT THAT DOESN'T
REQUIRE HIM TO BE PHYSICAL.
MAKING HIM AWARE OF THAT I THINK
HE JUST TOOK THE BALL AND RAN.
>> I THINK THE MOST DIFFICULT
PART ABOUT HAVING NO ARMS AND NO
LEGS IS SIMPLY NOT BEING ABLE TO
PLAY SPORTS.
I DON'T SHOW IT.
I'M GOOD AT NOT SHOWING IT BUT,
YEAH, I GET MAD.
I GET MAD AT GOD.
I GET MAD AT THE LORD.
LIKE WHY.
>> HIS FRESHMAN YEAR AND HE WAS
STANDING BEHIND THE FENCE AT A
DISTANCE WATCHING THEM PRACTICE.
THAT WAS THE BEGINNING.
>> WE WANTED TO GET HIM INVOLVED
IN THE PROGRAM SO INVITED HIM TO
BE OUR MANAGER.
>> THEY DIDN'T KNOW WHAT I COULD
DO.
THEY OBVIOUSLY KNEW I COULDN'T
PLAY BUT TO INCLUDE ME MADE ME
FEEL A PART OF IT.
MADE ME FEEL I GUESS YOU CAN SAY
NORMAL.
>> HE PAID ATTENTION TO US AS
COACHES BUT HE LEARNED THE GAME
BY MADDEN FOOTBALL.
HE CREATED GAME PLANS ON MADDEN
AND THEN HE'D COME TO PRACTICE
AND TRY TO CREATE THE SAME GAME
PLANS AND EXECUTE THEM THE SAME
WAY.
I STARTED TO GIVING ROBERT A
LITTLE MORE RESPONSIBILITY WITH
MY QUARTERBACKS.
>> EYES ON THE QUARTERBACK.
EYES ON THE QUARTERBACK.
>> AND THE NEXT THING YOU KNOW
HE WAS THERE RUNNING THE DRILLS
FOR US.
>> GO, GO, GO, GO.
WHEN YOU ROLL OUT, BIG EYES.
BIG EYES, OKAY.
>> HIS ABILITY TO STUDY THE GAME
AND HIS ABILITY TO TRANSLATE
THOSE THINGS TO THE KIDS IS
UNMATCHED BY MOST OF THE COACHES
THAT I KNOW.
>> RIGHT IN FRONT OF THE LINE.
RAM OVER.
W 6 ORBIT.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> AWESOME.
>> I'VE BEEN OVERLOOKED THE LAST
THREE OR FOUR YEARS I'VE BEEN
READY FOR IT.
>> WHEN I GO TO A JOB INTERVIEW
I FEEL LIKE SOMETIMES SCARING IS
NOT THE RIGHT WORD.
SURPRISES AND I DON'T THOUGH HOW
THEY'LL TAKE THE SURPRISE.
>> AS HE ROLLS OUT, TO BE
BRUTALLY HONEST WHEN I SAW THAT,
HOW CAN THIS GUY COACH.
AND AS HE COMES CLOSE, GIVE ME A
FIST PUMP.
GIVE ME A FIST PUMP.
I JUST GIVE HIM A FIST PUMP ON
THE SHOULDER AND ALL THAT NERVES
THAT I HAD WAS JUST MELTED AWAY.
WE HAD OTHER POLITICS SO I KNEW
IN MY HEART THAT HE WOULD BE A
GREAT FIT FOR THESE YOUNG
ATHLETES.
>> I REMEMBER WHEN COACH HIRED
ME AND RECRUITED ME OFF CAMPUS,S
OF LIKE, YES, I FELT REALLY
ACCOMPLISHED BECAUSE IT TOOK ME
SO LONG.
I KNEW I'VE BEEN READY FOR IT
AND I'VE BEEN OVERLOOKED AND
FINALLY SOMEONE GAVE ME THE
OPPORTUNITY SO I REALLY
APPRECIATED THAT.
>> AT THIS TIME I JUST WANT TO
INTRODUCE TO YOU YOUR NEW JV
HEAD COACH, ROB MENDEZ.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> APPRECIATE THAT, COACH CABLE.
THANK YOU, COACH.
YOU KNOW, FOOTBALL IS MY
PASSION.
I CAN'T WAIT TO GET TO KNOW
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF YOU.
BELIEVE IN YOURSELF, YOUR
TEAMMATES AND WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
ARE WE CLEAR, GENTLEMEN?
>> YES, SIR.
>> I'M EXCITED, GUYS.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> OBVIOUSLY IT WAS A LITTLE
SHOCKING AND THERE WAS JOKES
GOING AROUND.
TYPICAL TEENAGERS, YOU KNOW, A
GUY WITH NO ARMS OR LEG, NOT A
LOT OF PEOPLE HAVE SEEN THAT.
>> IF YOU'RE TAKEN BACK THAT'S
JUST NATURAL AND THAT'S HUMAN.
BUT AFTER THE FIRST TWO SECONDS,
IT'S JUST A NORMAL GUY.
>> I DON'T CARE HOW GOOD YOU
ARE, I DON'T CARE HOW
EXPERIENCED YOU ARE, YOU GUYS
ARE GOING TO DO EVERYTHING AS A
TEAM.
>> THOUGH HE MAY NOT LOOK LIKE A
COACH HE DEFINITELY ACTS LIKE
ONE.
>> 157.
>> SO WHAT WE'LL TEACH RIGHT NOW
IS CALLED 31 ZONE.
>> HIS KNOWLEDGE OF THE GAME
TORE SOMEBODY THAT HASN'T
ACTUALLY GONE THROUGH IT IS
IMPRESSIVE.
ON HIS PHONE HE CAN DIAGRAM A
PLAY FASTER THAN I CAN DO WITH A
PEN AND PAPER.
>> THERE'S DEFINITELY DOUBTERS
OUT THERE LIKE PARENTS, LIKE MY
SON IS GETTING COACHED BY A
QUARTERBACK WITH A GUY WITH NO
ARMS AND NO LEGS.
THAT LIGHTS A FIRE UNDER MY BUTT
AND PROBABLY GETS ME EXCITED
BECAUSE I REALLY JUST TRY TO
PROVE PEOPLE WRONG ABOUT IT.
>> WHEN THEY SEE HIM AND WITNESS
HIM AND HEAR HIM, I'D LIKE TO
BELIEVE THAT THEY TAKE A MOMENT
TO EVALUATE THEMSELVES AND
ANYTHING THAT THEY'VE GONE
THROUGH IN LIFE CAN'T BE MORE
DIFFICULT THAN WHAT HE ENDURES
ON A DAILY BASIS.
>> ONE THING I CARE ABOUT MORE
THAN ANYTHING IS BEING A FAMILY.
THAT IS ONE THING I TAKE PRIDE
ON.
I LOVE PEOPLE.
I LOVE YOU, I LOVE, I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE EVERYONE.
SO IF YOU GUYS CAN'T GET ALONG,
YOU BETTER GET OFF ME.
>> WHOM AM I GOING TO GO TO?
>> SO, SO, SO.
>> IT WAS A FRACTURED ORBIT TALL
BONE AND MY CHEEKBONE WAS
FRACTURED AS WELL.
I COULDN'T SLEEP.
I COULDN'T CHEW.
>> I JUST FELT BAD FOR HIM.
HE'S GOT A HARD LIFE.
I TRY TO MAKE IT AS EASY AS I
CAN.
>> THINGS THAT YOU AND I TAKE
FOR GRANTED LIKE BRUSHING YOUR
TEETH OR WASHING YOUR FACE OR
TAKING A SHOWER OR GOING TO THE
RESTROOM, ROBERT NEEDS SOMEONE
TO HELP HIM.
BUT HE'S TOUGH.
TWO DAYS LATER EVANS AT HIS
PRACTICE.
>> WIDEN OUT.
WIDEN OUT BOTH OF YOU.
>> HIS THING IS, NO, I GOT TO BE
THERE FOR THE KIDS.
>> GO TO THE FLACK.
>> HE'S BEEN WAITING TO BE A
HEAD COACH FOR A LONG TIME.
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO LET THEM
DOWN.
I DIDN'T WANT TO LET THE KIDS
I JUST CAN'T STAY AWAY, I GUESS.
ME BEING CHALLENGED HAS BEEN MY
MOTIVATION.
>> ALL I GOT TO SAY IS WHO SAYS
I CAN'T.
[ CHANTING "NOBODY" ]
>> WHO SAYS I CAN'T ORIGINALLY
CAME FROM KNEE JUST HAVING A
DRIVE TO ACCOMPLISH WHATEVER
PEOPLE DOUBTED ME FOR.
>> WHO SAYS I CAN'T.
NOBODY.
WHO SAYS I CAN'T.
>> YEAH!
>> HE'S WILLING TO DO ALL OF
THAT.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
>> IT'S GO TIME.
WE'VE BEEN WORKING HARD ALL
SUMMER LONG.
ON THREE, ONE, TWO, THREE.
OKAY, GUYS, LET'S GO.
LET'S GO.
38 STRETCH.
>> TOUCHDOWN.
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
SAMMY, LET'S GO.
>> THOSE KIDS FOUGHT EVERY
SINGLE GAME.
I CAN'T REMEMBER ONE GAME WE
WERE BIGGER THAN THE OTHER TEAM
BUT WE GOT THE JOB DONE.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
WE GOT THE MOMENTUM.
KEEP IT UP.
LET'S GO.
>> THEY'VE HAD MOSTLY LOSING
SEASONS.
HE JUST REALLY HAS DONE A JOB
THAT I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO SEE
OTHER COACHES DO AT THAT LEVEL
BEFORE.
>> I'M TRAINED TO SEND THEM OVER
THE MIDDLE BECAUSE IT'S GOING TO
BE RIGHT HERE OVER THE MIDDLE.
>> LET'S GO.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S GOOD.
APPRECIATE IT, GUYS.
LET'S GO.
>> WHO SAYS I CAN'T.
WHAT?
WHO SAYS I CAN'T?
>> GOOD MORNING AND HELLO,
PROSPECT AND SOPRANO HIGH.
WINNER TODAY WINS THE LEAGUE.
>> REMEMBER THIS, I'M PROUD OF
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF YOU.
WE'RE NOT DONE YET SO LET'S
FINISH THE JOB OFF RIGHT NOW.
>> MIGHT TAKE A MIRACLE PLAY TO
SCORE THE ONLY POINTS OF THIS
CONTEST.
INTERCEPTED.
4:37 TO PLAY IN THE FOURTH
QUARTER.
LOOKING FOR THE FIRST POINT.
KICK ON THE WAY.
HAS THE DISTANCE AND IT'S GOOD.
AND SOPRANO TAKES A 3-0 LEAD.
>> ACTUALLY GUYS, THIS RIGHT
HERE, 180 SMASH.
>> FOURTH AND 14 FOR THE
PANTHERS.
FOURTH DOWN PLAY, JACKSON ON TO
HIS LEFT AND IT'S INCOMPLETE.
SOPRANO GETS THE WIN AND TAKES
THE DIVISION TITLE WITH A WIN
THIS AFTERNOON OVER PROSPECT.
>> COME ON.
>> THAT WAS THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING TO REMEMBER THAT, OKAY.
THAT'S WHY WE BUILT THIS TEAM
OFF WAS FAMILY.
WE GOT GOOD DAYS AND BAD DAYS
AND WE CAME THIS FAR AS A TEAM.
I'M VERY PROUD OF THIS TEAM.
IT'S GOING TO HURT TODAY.
AND THAT'S OKAY IF IT HURTS
BECAUSE WE CARED A LOT BECAUSE
WE LOVED THIS GAME OF FOOTBALL.
I REALLY SINCERELY WANT YOU GUYS
TO UNDERSTAND HOW MUCH I
APPRECIATE THIS.
YOU GUYS HAVE GIVEN ME A
LIFETIME OF MEMORIES.
>> OUR OPPONENTS, THEY'D ALWAYS
DOUBT HIM BECAUSE THEY SEE A MAN
IN A WHEELCHAIR.
TO US WE SEE OUR COACH WHO IS
PERFECT.
AFTER THE GAME, MAKES ME FEEL
LIKE PROUD TO HAVE HIM AS MY
COACH.
>> THESE KIDS WOULD FOLLOW HIM
NO MATTER WHERE HE GOES.
WE CAN SEE THE CHANGES IN THE
KIDS.
>> CAN I GET A HUG?
>> YOU WANT THE BEST FOR YOUR
CHILDREN AND I TOLD HIM ONE
TIME, NOT A LOT OF MONEY IN
THIS, ROBERT.
AND HE TOLD ME, NOT EVERYBODY
DOES WHAT THEY DO FOR MONEY.
HE'S RIGHT.
>> THEY GAVE ME THE FEELING OF
IMPORTANCE.
AND I DON'T THINK THEY KNOW THAT
AND UNDERSTAND THAT.
MAYBE THEY WILL ONE DAY BUT I
LOVE THOSE KIDS AND I'M ALWAYS
GOING TO REMEMBER THEM.
YEAH.
>> I THINK WE MAKE A PERFECT
TEAM.
CAN WE AGREE ON THAT.
>> YES, SIR.
>> CAN WE AGREE ON THAT.
>> WHO SAYS I CAN'T?
>> NOBODY.
>> YEAH!
>> WHILE SEVERAL SCHOOLS IN THE
SILICON VALLEY RECENTLY NOTIFIED
MENDEZ OF VARSITY HEAD COACHING
OPENINGS HE'S DECIDED NOT TO
INTERVIEW.
HE SAYS HE HAS UNFINISHED
BUSINESS WITH HIS JV TEAM AT
PROSPECTMENT FOR MORE ON ROB'S
REMARKABLE JOURNEY HEAD TO
ESPN+.
FOR THE HALF HOUR DEREK MASON
-- DOCUMENTARY YOU CAN STREAM
RIGHT NOW.
SEE HIM RECEIVE THE JIMMY V
AWARD FOR PER CERRA VEERNS.
WITH A.B. ON THE RAIDERS WHAT
MIGHT JUJU'S NEW ROLE BE IN
PITTSBURGH AS THE LEAGUE WIDE
RECEIVER WILL TAKE UP THAT TOPIC
NEXT.
>> KEEP UP WITH YOUR FAVORITE
TEAM ON THE GO.
WITH THE NFL APP.
GET ALL YOUR UPDATES, SCORES AND
LIVE GAMES DURING THE SEASON.
DOWNLOAD THE NFL APP FROM YOUR
APP STORE.
I got a very, very small loan
from my father.
You gotta start somewhere.
I'm a reporter for
The New York Times.
The when, the where
bank statements, tax returns,
it's out, dozens of copy records
of deeds and reports.
1995 showed that he was
bleeding money.
Go through it all,
understand it all
Holy sh**
Number by number,
brick by brick.
That's when we realized.
That's fraud.
I built this empire and
I did it by myself.
That's fraud.
Look! Make a wish!
I wish for a Biggie
Bag from Wendy's.
I wish everyone loved each
other and was always...
That's a great wish, Jimmy.
Get a Bacon Double stack with
a quarter pound of fresh beef,
nuggets, fries and a
drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
Ours is a proud bloodline.
We hail from the battlefields
to the badlands.
From the mountains
and the midtowns.
From the islands
to the highlands.
And directly to those who
understand...
That when you get behind the
wheel of a Jeep Wrangler.
You're joining a family.
Hurry in to the 4th of July
Sales Event and get $500
additional bonus cash
on select models.
Visit Jeep.com
What do you serve up
when that no name charcoal
burns out early?
Chicken tar tar?
Choose the charcoal
worth your flame.
Fastest lighting.
Longest burning.
For the way
barbecue should taste.
Kingsford.
>>> UFC 239 SATURDAY IN LAS
VEGAS.
TWO OF THE GREATEST CHAMPIONS
DEFENDING THEIR TITLE.
JOHN JONES VERSUS SANTOS AND
NUNES VERSUS HOLM.
GO TO ESPN+.COM/PAYPERVIEW.
>>> JUJU SMITH-SCHUSTER WILL
ENTER TRAINING CAMP WITH THE
PITTSBURGH STEELERS NUMBER ONE
WIDE RECEIVER FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN HIS CAREER.
HERE'S MR. SMITH-SCHUSTER ON
WHAT IT'S LIKE AND THE
EXPECTATION OF STEPING INTO THAT
ROLE.
>>> ALL THESE PEOPLE SAY YOU'RE
THE NUMBER ONE GUY THIS YEAR BUT
MORE FOR MYSELF I SEE MORE
OPPORTUNITY FOR ME AND OTHER
GUYS TO STEP UP.
A.B. HAVING 100 CATCHES OVER A
THOUSAND YARDS.
THOSE YARDS, THOSE CATCHES WILL
BE SPREAD OUT BETWEEN OUR
OFFENSE AND JAMES CONNER AND
JAMES WASHINGTON, DONTE UPON
CHIEF.
A LOT OF GAMES, JAMES SAMUELS.
THERE'S SO MANY GUYS THAT WILL
GET MORE TOUCH, MORE YARD, MORE
YAC TO HELP THEM INDIVIDUALLY.
AT THE END OF THE DAY I'M THE
SAME JUJU.
LAST YEAR I WAS 21, THIS YEAR
I'M 22 SAME THING.
>> THE OLDER WISER MORE MATURE
JUJU SMITH-SCHUSTER WITH A GOOD
JAC REFERENCE.
>> ALWAYS.
>> GOT US THINKING, OBVIOUSLY
BIG SHOES TO FILL WITH ANTONIO
BROWN DEPARTED.
HE'S NOW AN OAKLAND RAIDER SO
LET'S GO ONE BY ONE RECEPTIONS,
MORE OR LESS, RAN TONE YORE OWE
JUJU.
>> JUJU MADE ALL MY POINTS AND
WILL SPREAD THE BALL AROUND AND
HAVE A HEAD COACH IN JON GRUDEN
THE PLAY CALLER GAVE UP A LOT OF
MONEY, A.L. WILL HAVE MORE
RECEPTIONS.
>> I THINK JON GRUDEN IS
MOTIVATED TO GET BROWN THE
FOOTBALL.
>> TOUCHDOWNS.
>> A.B. AS WELL.
AND, YOU KNOW, YOU ACTUALLY TEED
ME UP PERFECTLY BECAUSE I THINK
IF THERE IS ANYONE THAT WANTS TO
MAKE ANTONIO BROWN WORK IN
OAKLAND BECAUSE THEY HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT WHY THEY GAVE HIM ALL
THE MONEY IT WOULD BE JON GRUDEN
SO HE'S CALLING ALL THE SHOTS
AND IN TERMS OF WIDE RECEIVERS
WE CAN DEBATE ALL DAY LONG WHO
IS THE BEST BUT KNOW HOW SPECIAL
A.B. CAN BE AND AS SOON AS HE
FIGURES OUT THAT CHEMISTRY WITH
DEREK CARR HE WILL HAVE MORE.
>> RECEPTION, TOUCHDOWNS AND HOW
ABOUT ALL PURPOSE YARDS, VICTOR
CRUZ.
>> I'LL GIVE JUJU SOME LOVE
HERE.
>> FINALLY.
>> MIKE AND DIANNA HAVE NOT
GIVEN HIM ANY LOVE BUT I'M
GIVING HIM YARDS.
IN THOSE PRESSURE SITUATIONS BEN
WILL LOOK FOR HIM TO BE THE
NUMBER ONE RECEIVER AND GET HIM
THE BALL IN SPACE AN DEEP ROUTES
AND CAN RUN ANY ROUTE IN THE
BOOK.
INTERESTING TO SEE HOW THEY USE
HIM AS THE NUMBER ONE GUY.
>> A TEAM GAME AND ALL OF THOSE
THINGS ARE WHAT THEY ARE.
WHAT REALLY MATTERS, OF COURSE,
YOU HOPE IS THE NUMBER OF WINS
FROM EACH TEAM.
WE GOT THE STEELERS AND RAIDERS.
WHO GETS THE EDGE.
>> PITTSBURGH, IMPROVEMENT WITH
OAKLAND ON OFFENSE, JOSH JACOB,
TERRELL WILLIAMS, A.B.
OBVIOUSLY, ANOTHER YEAR WITH
DEREK CARR AND JON GRUDEN REALLY
WORRIED ABOUT THE DEFENSE AND
THEY LOST KHALIL MACK.
WHILE THEY DRAFTED THOSE PLAYERS
FROM CLEMSON IN THE FIRST ROUND
IT WILL TAKE A WHILE TO GET
GOING AND BE A WORK IN PROGRESS
IN TERMS OF HOW THEY ARE ON
DEFENSE.
I'LL GO WITH MIKE TOMLIN AND
VERY MATURE PITTSBURGH STEELER
ORGANIZATION.
>> I THINK THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD
BET.
HOW ABOUT CELEBRATIONS?
IS THIS TEAM A QUESTION?
>> NOT A QUESTION AT ALL.
I'M GOING WITH JUJU MAIN LAY
BECAUSE IT DOESN'T EVEN HAVE TO
BE HIM TO SCORE TO DO THE
CELEBRATION.
>> HE'S MADE THAT CLEAR.
>> EVERYBODY IS IN ON THIS THING
WHETHER IT'S HIM OR McDONALD OR
ANY OTHER PERSON ON THAT TEAM
THEY'LL BE CELEBRATING AND JUJU
WILL BE LEADING THE WAY.
>> LET ME TELL YOU IF YOU DID
NOT SEE IT JUJU WAS WITH US
ABOUT AN HOUR AGO AND SAID HE IS
WORKING ON BEN ROETHLISBERGER TO
GET HIM INVOLVED.
HE'S NOT COMMITTED BUT TRYING.
VALIANT EFFORT.
WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT.
THE RESIDENT CELEBRATION EXPERT
FOR US.
LIKE ANYTHING CELEBRATION WE
HAVE TO GO TO HIM.
>> HERE I AM TAKING A BOW FOR
YOU.
>> WE HAVE ONE MORE CATEGORY.
HOW ABOUT THE DRAMA.
>> UH-OH.
>> THE DRAMA.
>> IS IT ON THERE OR NO.
>> WE'LL SEE HERE.
>> I GUESS NOT.
ALL RIGHT.
>> WE'LL JUST DO THE DRAMA.
>> I'M GOING TO GO WITH WHAT
HISTORY SAYS AND I THINK IT'S
GOING TO BE ANTONIO BROWN ON
THIS AND I'LL STICK WITH THAT.
I LIKE THE WAY JUJU
SMITH-SCHUSTER IS MATURING INTO
NOT JUST A MENTOR TO THESE
YOUNGER PLAYERS BUT AN ACTUAL
LEADER ON THE STEELERS TEAM AND
FOR ANTONIO BROWN THERE ARE A
LOT OF PERSONALITIES ON THE
ROSTER.
JON GRUDEN IS THE FOCAL POINT OF
THIS TEAM NO MATTER WHO IS ON IT
BUT I THINK THERE'S GOING TO BE
POINTS DURING THE SEASON WHERE
THE A.B. OF PITTSBURGH WILL SHOW
ITS FACE IN OAKLAND.
YOU CANNOT -- WE WILL NOT GET TO
THIS SEASON WITHOUT HIM GETTING
IRKED WITH DEREK CARR.
NO WAY.
>> IT TAKES ONE BALL ENALE HE BE
LIKE, REALLY.
>> PUT SOME MONEY ON IT.
THE ESPYS ARE RIGHT AROUND THE
CORN EVER.
WHO IS GETTING YOUR VOTE FOR THE
BEST RECORD-BREAKING
PERFORMANCE?
COME ON.
YOU KNOW DREW BREES WANTS YOUR
VOTE.
>> DREW BREES HAS DONE IT.
>> THE NFL'S ALL-TIME LEADING
PASSER.
>> YOU'RE IN THE WAR ZONE,
RIGHT.
(Client's Voice)
Remember that degree
you got in taxation?
(Danny)
Of course you don't
because you didn't!
Your job isn't
understanding tax code...
it's understanding why that...
will get him a body like that...
MOVE!
...that.
Your job isn't
doing hard work...
Here.
...it's making
her do hard work...
...and getting paid for it.
(VO)
Snap and sort your expenses to
save over $4,600 at tax time.
(Danny)
Jody...
...it's time to get yours!
(VO)
QUICKBOOKS. BACKING YOU.
This is Ode
to State Farm
winning five
J.D. Power
awards in a row
for life insurance.
( ♪♪ )
In B minor.
Woman:
Great stuff.
(VO)
The hamsters, run hopelessly in
their cage.
Content on their endless quest,
to nowhere.
( ♪♪ )
But perhaps this year, a more
exhilarating endeavor awaits.
Defy the Laws of human nature,At
the summer of Audi sales event.
Get Exceptional Offers now.
So I can buy from
Enterprise Car Sales and you'll
take ANY trade-in?
That's right!
Great!
Here you go...
Well, it does need
to be a vehicle.
But - I need this out of
my house.
(VO) With fair, transparent
value for every trade-in...
Enterprise makes it easy.
>>> DREW BREES FINDS HIHIMSELF
ONLYLY 35 YARDS AWAY.
>> IT'S ABOUT OUR STRENGTH.
>> JUST PEYTON MANNING LEFT TO
PASS.
>> HE STARTS IN THE SHOTGUN.
DROPS BACK.
LOOKS TO THE FAR SIDELINE.
WIDE OPEN AND WHAT A WAY TO DO
IT.
>> UH-OH.
>> DREW BREES IS THE NFL'S
ALL-TIME LEADING PASSER.
>> HEY, BOYS.
HOW ABOUT THAT, HUH.
>> ONLY ONE WORD THAT COMES TO
MIND.
GREATNESS.
>> WELL, WE CONTINUE TO
HIGHLIGHT SOME OF THE STAVETSKIS
AND THE NFL THAT EARNED ESPY
NOMINATIONS THIS YEAR.
THE AMAZING MOMENT FROM DREW
BREES IS UP FOR THE ESPY FOR
BEST RECORD-BREAKING
PERFORMANCE.
BREES BROKE THE PASSING RECORD
WHEN HE PASSED PEYTON MANNING'S
MARK AND, VICTOR, YOU MADE THIS
POINT YESTERDAY, IT'S TRUE.
I THINK LAST YEAR WAS HIS BEST
BET AT WINNING MVP.
YOU JUST HAD THIS PESKY PATRICK
MAHOMES WHO DID THINGS THAT JUST
DIDN'T SEEM POSSIBLE TO KEEP
BREES FROM WINNING THAT AWARD.
>> EXACTLY.
HOW DO YOU AMASS SUCH A
MONUMENTAL RECORD LIKE THIS ON
AN ILLUSTRIOUS AND NOT WIN THE
LEAGUE MVP ONE TIME.
PEYTON MANNING, TOM BRADY, HE'S
GOT TO GET IT ONE TIME.
HE'S PUTTING UP NUMBERS EACH AND
EVERY YEAR AND THERE ARE YEARS
HE GOES UNDER THE RADAR WITH
THOSE PLAYMAKERS AND EVERYBODY
HE HAS.
THIS IS A YEAR, LET'S PUT A NICE
PRETTY RED BOW ON THIS CAREER
AND PUT A LEAGUE MVP UNDER MY
BELL AND GET BACK TO THE BIG
DANCE HOPEFULLY AND KEEP THINGS
GOING.
>> SO IN FAIRNESS HE HAS BEEN A
SUPER BOWL MVP, TWO-TIME
OFFENSIVE PLAYER OF THE YEAR.
BUT, YOU KNOW, THE WHOLE THING,
QUALITY QUARTERBACK OF DREW
BREES, HE WOULD TAKE A LOMBARDI
TROPHY ANY DAY OF THE WEEK.
>> AT LEAST GIVE HIM ONE LEAGUE
MVP.
HE'S EARNED IT.
>> HOW ABOUT THE BEST OF THE
BEST OF DREW BREES.
>> THIS IS VINTAGE RIGHT HERE.
>> VINTAGE.
'04.
PLAY ACTION, DEEP TO ERIC
PARKER, BREAKS A TACKLE FOR A
79-YARD TOUCHDOWN.
>> I LIKE IT.
SHOWING THAT ARM OFF.
BLACK AND WHITE THERE.
>> REAL EARLY.
PIXELATED.
GRAINY, I LOVE IT.
>> PIXELATED.
>> THERE YOU GO.
2014 AGAINST THE PACKERS.
THREE STEPS UP.
JUST LAYS THIS ONE PERFECTLY
INTO THE ARMS OF BRANDIN COOKS.
A 50-YARD TOUCHDOWN STRIKE.
>> A DIME.
>> WHAT IS I DIME.
>> YOU SEE QUARTERBACKS STEP UP
IN THE POCKET KEEPING HIS EYES
DOWN THE FIELD.
PUTS SO MUCH PRESSURE ON THE
DEFENSE.
>> '06 AGAINST THE BENGAL,
HANDOFF HERE.
A FLEAFLICKER.
>> LOVE IT.
>> AND THEN JOE HORN THERE
BETWEEN TWO DEFENDERS, A 72-YARD
TOUCHDOWN AND IT'S THAT KIND OF
ARM THAT WE SEE.
>> HEY, I LIKE IT.
I LIKE IT.
>> MOVING NOW TO THE MODERN DAY.
>> MISS THAT.
>> TO TED GINN IN THE END ZONE.
>> CONSISTENCY WE'RE SEEING HERE
IS -- HE'S NOT EVEN BEING
TOUCHED.
BARELY PEOPLE AROUND HIM WHILE
HE'S MAKING THESE THROWS LIKE
THAT'S INDICATIVE TO THE TYPE OF
TEAM HE'S BEEN AROUND.
THAT OFFENSIVE LINE TAKES GOOD
CARE OF HIM.
>> '06 CHAMPIONSHIP, SAINTS AND
BEARS.
BREES TO REGGIE BUSH.
>> GREAT EXAMPLE OF AN EFFECTIVE
QUARTERBACK PLAY.
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO THROW AS
HARD AS YOU CAN.
THAT WAS A GREAT TOUCH THROW TO
THE RUNNING BACK WHO TAKES IT
ALL THE WAY.
WHAT TOUCH HE HAS.
SUCH AN UNDERRATED ASPECT OF
PLAYING QUARTERBACK.
>> THEN 2016 AGAINST THE
RAIDERS, THE LONGEST CAREER
PASS, A 90 -- THIS SAYS 98 -- I
ALWAYS HAVE TO -- YARDS AFTER --
BRANDIN COOKS.
AN INCREDIBLE CAREER.
>> PERHAPS A FUTURE NFL MVP.
YOU CAN VOTE ON THE ESPYS AT
ESPYS.COM.
AGAIN, BREES UP FOR
RECORD-BREAKING PERFORMANCE
ALONG WITH THREE OTHER MOMENTS
INCLUDING CLAY THOMPSON'S RECORD
FOR THREE-POINTERS IN A GAME
WITH 14.
ALL RIGHT.
WE GAVE YOU OUR UPON.
WHO ARE YOU HIGHLIGHTS.
SAQUON, KYLER.
LET US KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING
NEXT.
>>> IF YOU WANT A CROWN, I'LL
CROWN YOU BUT THEY ARE WHO WE
THOUGHT THEY WERE.
♪
Give Extra, get extra
with new Extra Refreshers gum.
[SFX: hawk screaming]
[SFX: bottle opening]
[SFX: water noises]
[SFX: water splashing]
[SFX: crackling noise]
[SFX: bottle opening]
[SFX: whistling noise]
[SFX: crackling noise]
Look! Make a wish!
I wish for a Biggie
Bag from Wendy's.
I wish everyone loved each
other and was always...
That's a great wish, Jimmy.
Get a Bacon Double stack with
a quarter pound of fresh beef,
nuggets, fries and a
drink for just five bucks.
Wendy's Biggie Bag is
everything you could wish for.
Thanks for the
ride-along, Captain!
I've never been in
one of these before,
even though GEICO has been-
Ohhh.
Ooh ohh here we go,
here we go.
You got cut off there,
what were you saying?
Oooo. Oh no no.
Maybe that GEICO has been
proudly serving the military
for over 75 years?
Is that what you
wanted to say?
Mhmmm.
I have to say, you seemed
a lot chattier on TV.
GEICO. Proudly serving the
military for over 75 years.
You OK back there, buddy?
How do you gauge the
greatness of an SUV?
Is it to carry cargo
or to carry on a legacy?
Its show of strength
or its sign of intelligence?
In crossing harsh terrain
or breaking new ground?
This is the time to get
an exceptional offer
on the Mercedes of
your midsummer dreams
at the Mercedes-Benz Summer
Event, going on now.
Lease the GLA 250 SUV
for just $329 a month
at the Mercedes-Benz
Summer Event.
Mercedes-Benz.
The best or nothing.
>> Announcer: "NFL LIVE" IS
BROUGHT TO YOU BY GEICO.
15 MINUTES COULD SAVE YOU 15% OR
MORE ON CAR INSURANCE.
>>> TELL ME ALL ABOUT IT.
>> CANADIAN FOOTBALL LEAGUE
ACTION THURSDAY ON ESPN.
IT'S THE 3-0 HAMILTON TIGER CATS
TAKING ON THE MONTREAL ALOUETTES
AT 7:30 EASTERN.
VISIT US ESPN+.COM AND DO NOT
FORGET "SPORTSCENTER" 6:00
EASTERN AFTER THE GET UP NBA
FREE AGENCY SPECIAL WITH KEVIN
NEGHANDI AND MICHAEL EAVES AND
THE LATEST ON KAWHI'S DECIDING
FACTORS PLUS ANALYSIS FROM THE
U.S. WOMEN.
THEIR SEMIFINAL AGAINST INC.
DPAPDZ AND DAY TWO AT WIMBLEDON
AT 6:00 AND THE ESPN APP.
EVERYBODY STATE THEIR CASE.
NOT A REAL ESPY BUT WE'RE
HANDING ONE OUT, THE NFL
HIGHLIGHT KING.
AND DIANNA RUSSINI, WHO MADE THE
CASE FOR PATRICK MAHOMES.
I DON'T KNOW, GUYS.
I HAPPEN TO AGREE.
THE MAN IS A HIGHLIGHT MACHINE.
>> HE IS.
>> I WANT TO THROW A CHALLENGE
FLAG.
THE NFL, RIGHT?
WE HAVEN'T HAD ANY NFL PLAYS FOR
KYLER.
>> WHAT YOU'RE SAYING -- YOU
WERE SAYING YOU WERE HANDICAPPED
FROM THE GET-GO.
>> OKAY.
>> NO CRYING IN THE BIG LEAGUES,
MIKE.
>> PUT THE PRESSURE ON YOU.
ARE YOU GOING WITH TEAM VIC SORE
AND SAQUON BARKLEY OR PATRICK
MAHOMES.
>> I'M A FREE AGENT.
I'M FROM THE HIGHEST BIDER.
>> SEE HOW IT WORKS.
>> OFFSCREEN.
>> JULY 4th HOLIDAY.
WE WANT TO SAY A SPECIAL THANK
U