.
>> WE WILL TIME-OUT HOUR BY
HOUR WHEN SNOW COMES IN AND
WHEN IT TURNS TO SLEET AND
FREEZING RAIN.
>> JUST A TERRIBLE TRAGEDY.
CHILDREN OH SO SCARRED BY THIS
CRIME.
>> DO YOU THINK BRYCE HARPER IS
COMING BACK.
>> PART OF ME SAYS NO AND PART
OF ME SAYS YES.
>> GOT A LOT TO TALK ABOUT.
I SAT DOWN WITH NOTED SCHOLAR
AND JESUIT PRIEST FATHER THOMAS
READ EARLIER FOR AN
CONVERSATION ABOUT SEX ABUSE IN
THE CATHOLIC CHURCH.
FIRST WE NEED TO BRING YOU UP-
TO-DATE ON THE WEATHER.
A RED WEATHER ALERT's BEE
SNOWFALL TOTALS A LITTLE BIT
DOESN'T DIMINISH THE IMPACT OF
THE STORM.
THIS HAS ELEMENTS THAT ARE
DANGEROUS WITH SLEET AND
FREEZING RAIN.
GAITHERSBURG, WURZBURG, WURZBURG
, HAGERSTOWN TO THE MOUNTAINS,
1 -THREE IMMEDIATE METRO, D.C.,
CHEVY CHASE, BETHESDA AND
SOUTH.
NOT AS MUCH.
TRACED TO AN INCH.
COLD AIR LACKING A BIT.
THE ROAD IS GOING TO BE A
DISASTER TO GET INTO WEDNESDAY
MORNING.
RPM UP TO ITS OLD TRICKS AGAIN,
7 INCHES EVERYONE ELSE HAS A
GRASP ON REALITY  2 - 3 INCHES.
WE KNOW THAT SNOWFALL WILL BE
MODERATE TO HEAVY 6:00 A.M.
TO NOON AND ROADS WILL BECOME
TREACHEROUS AND WHEN IT STARTS
IT WILL PICK UP IN INTENSITY,
QUICKLY AND ACCUMULATE QUICKLY.
SNOW WILL GO TO A MIX NORTHWEST
IN THE AFTERNOON AND RAIN D.C.
SELF IN EAST IN THE AFTERNOON.
IF WE CAN GET THROUGH THE DAY
IT WILL TURN ALL RAIN MIGHT
TOMORROW NIGHT AFTER MORNING
SHOWERS ON THURSDAY.
LOOK HOW MUCH MOISTURE IS
HEADED OUR WAY.
IF THE SYSTEM WERE 300 MILES
OFF TO THE EAST COULD BE
LOOKING AT A BLIZZARD BUT WE
ARE NOT.
5:00 A.M.
A LITTLE SNOW BREAKING OUT
PARTS OF THE METRO TEMPS UPPER
20s LOW 30s BECOMES HEAVY TO
MODERATE ACROSS THE ENTIRE
METRO BY 7:00 ON WEDNESDAY.
TEMPS 2930 DEGREES.
10:00 HEAVY SNOW ACROSS THE
METRO AND IT BEGINS TO MIX AND
CHANGE AROUND THE LUNCH HOUR.
WHEN WE COME BACK WE WILL TALK
ABOUT HOW MUCH ICE WILL
ACCUMULATE AND WHO IS MOST MOST
LIKELY TO HAVE A POWER OUTAGE.
>>> IF MANNY MACHADO IS GETTING
300 MILLION WHAT WILL BRYCE
HARPER GET?
MACHADO HAS AGREED TO SIGN WITH
THE SAN DIEGO PADRES REPORTEDLY
WORTH $300 MILLION OVER TEN
YEARS.
THE DEAL PENDING RESULTS OF THE
PHYSICAL.
THE FORMER BALTIMORE OREO SAID
THE L.A.
DODGERS INFIELDER IS SET TO
PLAY 3rd  BASE.
NOW THE ATTENTION TURNS TO
BRYCE HARPER.
SPECULATION ALL OVER SOCIAL
MEDIA.
WILL HE RE-SIGN WITH THE
NATIONALS?
MOST DON'T THINK SO.
LATEST RUMORS HAVING GOING TO
PHILADELPHIA.
THE PLAYERS ALREADY IN SPRING
TRAINING CAMP IN FLORIDA.
BUT DARREN HAYNES SAT DOWN WITH
DAVEY MARTINEZ TO TALK ABOUT IT
.
>> Reporter: HOW MUCH YOU WANT
PRICE ON YOUR TEAM?
>> GREECE AND I HAVE A SPECIAL
RELATIONSHIP.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT.
WHO WOULDN'T WANT BRYCE HARPER
ON YOUR TEAM?
HONESTLY?
ONE OF THE BEST YOUNG PLAYERS
IN THE GAME.
AND FOR ME IT'S ALL ABOUT WHAT
HE WANTS. FOR HIS FAMILY AND
HIS CAREER.
IT REALLY IS.
HE'S GOT BIG DECISIONS TO MAKE.
I WOULD BE WRONG TO SAY THAT OF
COURSE, ANYBODY WOULD WANT HIM
ON HIS TEAM.
>> IF BRYCE DECIDED I'M COMING
BACK TO THE NATIONALS, WHAT
WOULD BE YOUR REACTION IF HE
WALKED IN THE DOOR?
>> WELCOME BACK.
>> THAT'S IT?
>> TIME TO WORK.
GO TO WORK.
>> DO YOU THINK BRYCE HARPER IS
GOING BACK?
>> PART OF ME SAYS NO, PART OF
ME SAYS YES.
THE WAY THIS GAME IS YOU DON'T
KNOW.
YOU REALLY DON'T KNOW.
>> Reporter: WHICH WAY ARE YOU
LEANING?
>> HONESTLY, LIKE I SAID, I
CAN'T LEAN EITHER WAY.
IT IS SO WEIRD BECAUSE, YOU
KNOW?
LIKE I SAID I TRIED TO SAY HEY,
YOU KNOW WHAT, THIS IS WHAT
I'VE GOT TO DO TODAY.
I'VE GOT TO LEAD 59 GUYS
TOMORROW MORNING, GET UP AT 6:00
, GET TO THE BALLPARK AND GET
THE DAY GOING.
MY FOCUS IS ON THE DAY AT HAND,
THE HERE AND NOW AND THAT IS
WHAT I'M WORRIED ABOUT.
EAT YOUR FOOD, MAN.
>> IS MARTINEZ PLAYING US?
HOW DOES HE NOT KNOW?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF HE DOES.
I THINK THERE IS A BIG QUESTION
MARK IT.
MANNY MACHADO JUST SIGNED FOR
THE LARGEST FREE-AGENT DEAL IN
THE HISTORY OF AMERICAN SPORTS,
SUCH AS BASEBALL.
THERE IS BIG PRESSURE ON
BRYCE'S AGENT TO GO AT LEAST 1
DOLLAR OVER THAT.
THE NATIONALS HAVE OFFERED 300
MILLION.
I DON'T KNOW IF THE OFFER IS
THERE ANYMORE.
WHAT DAVEY MARTINEZ IS THINKING,
AS TED LERNER BROKE HIS
PENDENCY WITH SCOTT MORRISON
ONLY HAS A BUNCH OF CLIENTS
BEFORE, CAN HE SAY NO TO HIM
THIS TIME?
I THINK THAT'S GOING TO BE THE
QUESTION.
PERSONALLY I WANT BRYCE TO
STAY.
HE IS STAR POWER.
>> RELAX STARS.
>> WITH JERSEYS ON THE BACK
THAT SORT OF THING.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> MY GUT IS THE PHILLIES WILL
OFFER SOMETHING SO ENORMOUS,
ONE PERSON SAID NINE YEARS,
$367 MILLION, I DON'T KNOW IF
THAT WILL HAPPEN OR NOT.
I KNOW THAT THE NATIONALS WILL
BE GIVEN A CHANCE TO COUNTER.
I JUST CAN'T.
BASED ON PAYROLL, BASED ON WHAT
THEY HAVE COMMITTED ALREADY BUT
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT COULD BE A WILDCARD.
>> THE NATS HAVE SOMEONE IN
BRYCE'S POSITION RIGHT NOW.
DOES THAT MATTER?
>> ROBLES, SOTO, DEFINITELY
GOING TO TAKE HIS SPOT AT THE
PLAY.
THEY ARE GOING TO BE BRYCE
HARPER.
BRYCE HARPER WAS A LIVE WIRE, A
HAND GRENADE.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW WHEN HE WOULD
EXPLODE.
THE MOST EXCITING THING IN
SPORTS.
>> THEY ALREADY BRING THOUSANDS
OF FANS HERE EVERY TIME THEY
PLAY.
>> PHILLIES FANS ARE THE WORST.
I LOVE YOU, I KNOW YOU, I WORKED
YOU BUT PHILLIES FANS OF THE
WORST.
>> THE SEXUAL ABUSE SCANDAL
THAT HAS SHAKEN THE CATHOLIC
CHURCH AT ITS CORE.
FOR US IT STARTS HERE IN
WASHINGTON D.C. FOR FORMER
CARDINAL AND ARCHBISHOP
THEODORE DID -- PETER MCCARRICK
HAS BEEN DEFROCKED BY THE POPE
LIVING IN A REMOTE MONASTERY
SOMEWHERE IN THE MIDWEST.
THEY ARE REPORTING CHILDREN
WERE SEXUALLY ABUSED FOR YEARS
BY PRIESTS WHO SHOULD HAVE BEEN
CARING FOR THEM.
YOU PROBABLY KNOW THAT POPE
FRANCIS HAS CALLED THE SUMMIT.
WE ARE TALKING WITH A NOTED
JESUIT PRIEST AND SCHOLAR. TELL
ME WHY YOU WERE GOING TO ROME
RIGHT NOW?
>> I AM GOING TO ROME BECAUSE
THE POPE HAS CALLED A MEETING
OF TOP BISHOPS FROM AROUND THE
WORLD TO COME AND TALK TO HIM
ABOUT THE SEX ABUSE CRISIS. HE
WANTS TO EMPHASIZE TO THEM HOW
IMPORTANT IT IS AND THEIR
RESPONSIBILITY AND I THINK HE
IS GOING TO MAKE THE POINT THAT
IF THEY ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE HE
WILL HOLD THEM ACCOUNTABLE.
THIS WILL BE AN IMPORTANT
MEETING FOR THE CATHOLIC CHURCH
BECAUSE THE FIRST MEETINGS LIKE
THIS THAT IS EVER HAPPENED.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
HEADLINES.
JUST TODAY THE WASHINGTON POST
IS REPORTING THAT DEAF CHILDREN
WERE SEXUALLY ABUSED BY PRIESTS
IN ARGENTINA.
IS THIS GOING TO COME UP IN
ROME?
>> THIS IS A TERRIBLE TRAGEDY.
CHILDREN ARE SO SCARRED BY THIS
CRIME, THIS ABUSE THAT THEY
SUFFER UNDER.
THAT IS WHY THE CHURCH HAS TO
HAVE A POLICY TO DEAL WITH IT.
UNITED STATES WE HAVE 0 POLICY
ON ABUSE OF CHILDREN. IN THE
CHURCH WE HAD THIS POLICY OF
ZERO-TOLERANCE SO ANY PRIEST
INVOLVED IN ABUSED IS REMOVED
FROM THE PRIESTHOOD.
THE SECOND PART IS TO MAKE SURE
ALL BISHOPS IMPLEMENT THIS
POLICY.
THAT IS AN IMPORTANT MESSAGE AT
THIS MEETING.
>> TALK TO ME ABOUT THE APPARENT
HYPOCRISY IN ALL THIS.
IT HAS COME OUT TODAY IN A NEW
YORK TIMES ARTICLE THAT THE
VATICAN HAS A BOOK, HAS RULES
ON WHAT TO DO WITH CHILDREN WHO
ARE BOTHERED BY PRIESTS?
WHO KNEW?
>> ACTUALLY WHEN YOU LOOK AT
THE DOCUMENT AND REPORTS I HAVE
SEEN THE EMPHASIS ON THE
PRIEST'S RESPONSIBILITY FOR HIS
CHILD.
POPE FRANCIS SAID THIS IN THE
PAST, HE SAID IT BEFORE HE
BECAME POPE AND THAT IS IF A
PRIEST FATHER'S A CHILD THAN HE
HAS A RESPONSIBILITY AS A FATHER
, FINANCIAL RESPONSIBILITY AND
JUST AS A FATHER THE PATERNAL
RESPONSIBILITY AND THAT
RESPONSIBILITY PRECEDES HIS
RESPONSIBILITY TO BE A PRIEST.
HE SHOULD LEAVE THE PRIESTHOOD
AND RAISE THE CHILD.
>> COMING UP MY CONVERSATION
CONTINUES.
Z35WDZ Z16FZ
Y35WDY Y16FY
.
>> THE POPE HAS SUMMONED CHURCH
LEADERS FROM AROUND THE WORLD
TO MEET AT THE VATICAN. WILL
THEY ADDRESS THE ISSUE OF
PRIESTS?
LET'S CONTINUE THE CONVERSATION
WITH FATHER THOMAS READ.
THIS PART OF THE CONNECTION
WASN'T AS CLEAR BUT -- WHAT
ABOUT THE ISSUE OF PRIESTS?
>> I WAS IN THE SEMINARY 100
YEARS AGO 13 GUYS IN MY CLASS
ONLY ONE BECAME A PRIEST.
I KNOW THAT JOHN WAS.
WE HAVE KNOWN ALL ALONG THERE
ARE PRIESTS.
IF IT WERE UP TO A LOT OF
CATHOLICS THERE WOULD BE OPENLY
PRIESTS, THERE WOULD BE WOMEN
PRIESTS, THERE WOULD BE MARRIED
PRIESTS WHO COULD HAVE
CHILDREN.
WHEN IS THE CHURCH GOING TO
COME TO THIS OR IS THIS WISHFUL
THINKING?
>> THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IS
THAT THERE ARE A LOT OF
WONDERFUL PRIESTS IN THE
PRIESTHOOD.
PRIESTS WHO OBSERVE THEIR VOW
OF CELIBACY AND ARE VERY GOOD
PASTORAL PRIESTS.
WE DON'T WANT TO MIX UP THE
ISSUE OF PRIESTS WITH THE ISSUE
OF SEXUAL ABUSE.
OF MINORS.
AND THAT CHECKPOINT NEEDS TO BE
MADE.
BUT I AGREE WITH YOU, I THINK
WE NEED FOR HONESTY IN THE
CHURCH.
FOR EXAMPLE, THE U.S. BISHOPS
HAVE NEVER LOVED ANYBODY TO
SURVEY PRIESTS TO FIND OUT WHAT
PERCENTAGE ARE.
WE HAVE ESTIMATES FROM TEN
-20-30-40-50-60.
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
NOBODY HAS ANY REAL DATA.
THE ONE FACT WE DO KNOW IF
THERE ARE PRIESTS MOST OF THEM
ARE GOOD PRIESTS WHO OBSERVE
THEIR PROMISE OF CELIBACY AND
ARE GOOD FOR THE CHURCH.
>> DO YOU EXPECT ANYTHING TO
COME OF THIS MEETING OR IS THIS
GOING TO BE MORE
WINDOWDRESSING?
>> I THINK MOST AMERICANS ARE
GOING TO BE DISAPPOINTED WITH
THIS MEETING BECAUSE WE WOULD
LIKE TO SEE POLICIES AND
PROCEDURES SET UP, STRUCTURES
TO HOLD BISHOPS ACCOUNTABLE.
I THINK THE TRUTH OF THE MATTER
IS THIS MEETING IS PRIMARILY FOR
OTHER COUNTRIES WHERE BISHOPS
ARE IN TOTAL DENIAL.
THEY DON'T THINK THEY HAVE THIS
PROBLEM.
THEY THINK THIS IS AN AMERICAN
IN THE MESSAGE WE WANT TO TAKE
IS DON'T MAKE THE SAME MISTAKES
THE AMERICAN BISHOPS DID.
GET YOUR ACT TOGETHER. MOVED
THE BAD PRIESTS AND HELP THE
VICTIMS IN HEALING.
>> IT IS NOT JUST THE PRIESTS.
WE'RE SEEING THEATER MCCARRICK
RIGHT HERE IN WASHINGTON WHO
HAS BECOME THE POSTER CHILD FOR
THIS KIND OF ABUSE.
NOT JUST PRIESTS, THE BISHOPS
ARE BEING ASKED TO POLICE
THEMSELVES ARE THEY NOT?
>> NO I THINK THIS IS VERY
IMPORTANT.
AND NEEDS TO BE DEALT WITH HE
WAS A RETIRED BISHOP THEY
BROUGHT THE INFORMATION TO THE
VATICAN AND THE VATICAN SAID
OKAY TREAT HIM JUST LIKE YOU
WOULD A PRIEST OF THE
ARCHDIOCESE OF NEW YORK.
HIS CASE WAS INVESTIGATED, THEY
HIRED A FORENSIC RESEARCH TEAM,
THE INFORMATION PRESENTED AND
THE ACCUSATIONS WERE CREDIBLE,
SUBSTANTIATED AND HE WAS REMOVED
AND HE REFINED A NOW REMOVED
FROM THE PRIESTHOOD.
HE IS NO LONGER BISHOP
MCCARRICK IS MR. MCCARRICK.
HE WILL NEVER BE A PRIEST
AGAIN.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT SHOULD
HAPPEN.
>> GOOD LUCK ON YOUR TRIP WE
LOOK FORWARD TO HEARING
REPORTS.
>>  THANK YOU.
GOOD TO BE WITH YOU.
>> WASHINGTON'S CURRENT
ARCHBISHOP IS OBVIOUSLY
LEAVING.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY WORD TONIGHT.
IF YOU MISSED PART ONE OF OUR
INTERVIEW, BOTH WILL BE POSTED
ON WUSA9.COM AFTER THIS
BROADCAST.
IT IS AN IMPORTANT CONVERSATION
. MAKE SURE TO CHECK IT OUT.
COMING UP A RED WEATHER ALERT
FOR TOMORROW, THE LATEST
TIMELINE ON
.
>>> LOOKING FOR A RED WEATHER
ALERT FOR SNOW AND SLEET AND
FREEZING RAIN.
HERE IS A LOOK AT THE SNOWFALL
MAP. 3 - 5 LEESBURG,
GAITHERSBURG OR FREDERICKSBURG.
IN THE METRO  1 - 3, LOWER THAN
YESTERDAY.
IS TAKING MORE SLEEP.
LET US KNOW INTO SOUTHERN
MARYLAND TRACE TO AN INCH
THERE.
NOTICE THE PLUS SIGN SOME OF
YOU COULD GET CONCEIVABLY OVER
5 INCHES WHICH IS GOING TO BE A
PROBLEM. WORRIED ABOUT THAT ONE
BACK TO THIS THE SECOND.
WE HAVE TO GET THROUGH SOME
THINGS TO GET TO SUNDAY.
GFS EUROPEAN MODEL PRETTY MUCH
IN AGREEMENT WITH US AROUND 3
INCHES.
SEEMS REASONABLE.
FROM WICHITA, KANSAS TO CAPE
HATTERAS SNOW EXTENDING UP IN
THE IOWA AND SOUTH DAKOTA AND
NEBRASKA I RESERVE THESE FOR
SNOW BECAUSE IF IT IS LEGITIMATE
ON THE FRONT AND IN TERMS OF
IMPACT WE KNOW IT'S COMING
HOPEFULLY FOLKS WILL STAY OFF
THE ROAD BUT NONETHELESS STILL
GIVE IT 3.5 IN THE IMPACT AS
WELL.
CERTAINLY A LEGITIMATE STORM.
I HAVE UPDATED THIS ON OUR
WEBSITE.
IN TERMS OF POWER OUTAGES,
ISOLATED ALONG I-95 AND POINTS
WEST, UNLIKELY EAST AND
SCATTERED OUT IN CUMBERLAND,
HAGERSTOWN. EVEN WHERE ICING
WILL OCCUR, 3 INCHES OF SNOW IN
D.C., PLAIN OLD-FASHIONED RAIN
WILL ADD TO THE WEIGHT OF THE
SNOW AND COULD BRING DOWN THOSE
AS WELL.
MACY POWER OUTAGES NOT CONFINED
TO JUST AREAS WITH ICE.
THIS IS ONE MODEL, MOST EYES
FOR THE WEST AND NOT THAT BAD.
GAITHERSBURG THREE TENTHS AND
CAN PROBABLY HANDLE IT.
NOW ALMOST AN INCH THREE TENTHS
LEESBURG, GAITHERSBURG THAT
WOULD CAUSE POWER OUTAGES.
WE START OUT WITH PEERS SNOW.
BUT THIS COLUMN OF AIR IS BELOW
FREEZING.
THAN WE GET WARM AIR AS IT
MOVES IN TO THE ATMOSPHERE
BECOME SLEET. FREEZING RAIN IS
WHAT WE ARE MOST CONCERNED ABOUT
, FALLS LIQUID BUT FREEZES ON
CONTACT.
WE ADJUSTED THE TIME A BIT.
HEAVY SNOW 6:00 A.M.
TO NOON.
ROADS WILL BECOME DANGEROUS.
THEY BECOME INTENSE QUICKLY AND
ACCUMULATE QUICKLY.
WE WILL GO TO MIX NORTH AND
WEST IN THE AFTERNOON.
RAIN D.C. SOUTH AND EAST IN THE
AFTERNOON.
HEAVY RAIN POSSIBLE OVERNIGHT
AND SHOWERS IN THE 50s ON
THURSDAY.
6:00 A.M.
TOMORROW SNOW ACROSS MOST OF
THE METRO.
THE DARK OF THE BLUE HEAVIER
SNOW.
9:00 NO DOUBT BUT IT BEGINS TO
TURN AS WE GET TOWARDS THE
LUNCH HOUR ESPECIALLY DOWN TO
THE SOUTH PLAIN OLD RAIN D.C.
SOUTH AND EAST BY 3:00.
SOME LINGERING FREEZING RAIN
NORTH AND WEST UNTIL THE
EVENING.
HERE WE GO RED ALERT WEDNESDAY
56 MORNING SHOWERS THURSDAY AND
NICE ON FRIDAY.
IN TERMS OF SNOW ONCE AGAIN
LOOKING AT  3 - 5 NORTH AND WEST
AND  1 - 3 IN THE METRO AND
TREES TO AN INCH
.
>> THE CAUSE OF THE WINTER
WEATHER, THE WASHINGTON TEAM
WILL BE ON EARLY TOMORROW WITH
THE LATEST ON CONDITIONS AND
CLOSINGS.
I AM ON TWITTER @BRUCEJOHNSON9.
SEE YO
Here's your Buick sir.
Actually, that's my Buick.
Your Buick doesn't have a
roof rack!
This is my Buick.
How are we gonna fit in your
mom's Buick?
Easy.
I like that new Buick.
Me too.
I was actually talking about
that Buick.
I knew that.
Did you?
Buick's fresh new lineup is full
of surprises.
Get great deals on our
expectation-shattering lineup.
Pay no interest for 72 months
on most Buick models.
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
♪♪