>>> COMING UP RIGHT NOW ON "PAGE
SIX TV" -- THE LATEST ON
SMOLLETT'S ATTACKERS.
CHICAGO PD IS STILL
INVESTIGATING.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHAT WE KNOW.
>>> AND ARE CARDI AND OFFSET
BACK TOGETHER?
WE'LL TELL YOU WHAT'S BEHIND THE
RUMORS.
>>> AND DECLARING WORK ON NEW
YORK CITY, NEW YORK.
HOW THE CITY IS CLAPPING BACK.
>>> AND RUE LA LA, BEVY WILL
BREAK IT DOWN.
WELCOME TO "PAGE SIX TV."
>>> WELCOME TO "PAGE SIX TV,"
TODAY WE'RE GOING TO LIVE THAT
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN!
AND THERE'S A LOT OF GOSSIP TO
GET TO AS THE STARS HEAD DOWN TO
HOTLANTA FOR THE SUPER BOWL!
AND CARDI B WHO MAY OR MAY NOT
BE BACK WITH OFFSET.
>> YEP.
>> LET'S TAKE IT INTO ANOTHER
STORY FIRST.
>> WE HAVE SERIOUS NEWS TO GET
TO.
WE WILL START WITH THE POEM
BREAK IN THE INVESTIGATION OF
THE BRUTAL ATTACK OF OUR FRIEND
"EMPIRE" STAR JUSSIE SMOLLETT.
POLICE SAID THEY FOUND FOOT AEMG
OF PEOPLE OF INTEREST.
THEY RELEASED FEETIOS LAST NIGHT
OF TWO PEOPLE WALKING AROUND THE
VICINITY WHERE JUSSIE SMOLLETT
WAS ALLEGEDLY ASSAULTED,
ALLEGEDLY HAND, IN THE 300 BLOCK
OF EAST NORTH WATER STREET IN
DOWNTOWN CHICAGO.
IT'S A VERY UPSCALE NEIGHBORHOOD
BUT APPARENTLY THAT BLOCK IS
PRETTY SCARY FROM WHAT PEOPLE
TELL ME.
WALKING THERE AROUND 2:00 A.M.
AT NIGHT.
REMEMBER JUSSIE WAS WALKING
ALONG WITH TWO MEN ALLEGEDLY
ATTACKED HIM AND YELLING RACIAL
SLURS AND HOMOPHOBIC SLURS AT
HIM AND THEY TIED A NOOSE AROUND
HIS NECK.
AND DOUSED HIM WITH AN UNKNOWN
SUBSTANCE.
>> IT'S HORRIBLE.
WE FOUND OUT FROM "VARIETY," WHO
WAS ON THE PHONE WITH HIS MUSIC
MANAGER NAMED BRANDON MOORE, AND
HE CONFIRMED TO POLICE HE WAS ON
THE PHONE WITH JUSSIE AT THE
TIME AND HE ACTUALLY TOLD US HE
HEARD THOSE WORDS MAGA COUNTRY
BEING YELLED, THAT'S WHAT JUSSIE
TOLD THE POLICE IS WHEN THEY HAD
RACIAL SLURS, THEY ALSO SAID
THIS IS MAGA COUNTRY OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
THIS IS WHAT BRIAN, HIS MANAGER
TOLD US, HE SAID I HEARD THAT
CLEARLY, I HEARD THE SCUFFLE AND
I HEARD THE RACIAL SLUR.
MORE DETAILS BEING CONFIRMED BY
HIM.
>> THANKFULLY, JUSSIE IS HOPE
RECOVERING.
HIS REP CON FIRMED HE WILL
PERFORM SATURDAY AT THE
TROUBADOUR IN LOS ANGELES.
WE LOVE THAT.
>> WE LOVE THAT.
THE SHOW MUST GO ON AND
JUSSIE SUCH A TROOPER.
I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE AFTER A
DEVASTATING, HORRIFIC ATTACK BUT
HE'S STILL DOING IT.
>> DEFINITELY A FIGHTER, MY
LOVE.
I AM NOT SURPRISED HE WILL SHOW
UP AND SHOW OUT, OUT THAT SHOW.
>> THE STORY IS STILL
DEVELOPING.
POLICE ARE LOOKING TO QUESTION
PEOPLE OF INTEREST IN THAT
VIDEO.
SO IF ANYONE HAS R HAS
INFORMATION CALL 310-747-8382 OR
REPORT IT ANONYMOUSLY AT CPD
TIPCOME.
AGAINST, THAT'S CPDTIP.COM.
>> THANK YOU, CARLOS.
WHAT IF I TOLD YOU YOU COULD WIN
TICKETS TO ANY BEYONCE AND JS
CONCERT FOR THE REST OF YOUR
LIFE?
OF COURSE WANT TO DO, RIGHT?
WHERE DO I SIGN UP.
THERE'S A CATCH THOUGH.
WHAT IF I TOLD YOU FOR THAT YOU
WOULD HAVE TO GO VEGAN?
>> EAT TOMATOES, YOU NAME IT,
VEGETABLES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SO BEYONCE AND JAY-Z TOOK TO
INSTAGRAM TO ANNOUNCE THIS NEW
CONTEST AS PART OF THE GREEN
PRINT PROJECT, WHICH GIVES FANS
A CHANCE TO LIVE A LIFE TIME OF
JAY AND BEY CONFERENCE TICKETS
IF THEY COMMIT TO A VEGAN PLAN.
AND IT HAS TO BE A PLANT-BASED
DIET.
SO IT'S FOR A GOOD CAUSE.
>> I THINK WE CAN CHEAT.
>>> MOVING ON, PETE DAVIDSON
DECLARED WEAR ON SYRACUSE, NEW
YORK CITY, AND NOW THE CITY MAY
BE FIGHTING BACK BY OPENING AN
INVESTIGATION INTO THE COMEDIAN.
HE FILMED HIS NEW MOVIE
"BIG-TIME ADOLESCENT" IN
SYRACUSE LAST SUMMER AND HE HAD
CHOICE WORDS FOR THE CITY WHEN
HE RECENTLY DROPPED BY THE
"VARIETY" STUDIO AT SUNDANCE.
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS EARLIER IN
THE WEEK BUT TAKE A LOOK ONCE
AGAIN.
>> IT SUCKS.
THE WHOLE TOWN OF SYRACUSE
BLOWS.
THEY FOUND OUT I WAS THERE AND
TRIED ARREST ME THE ENTIRE
TOMORROW.
THEY TRIED TO HUNT ME DOWN THE
ENTIRE TIME.
NEVER AGAIN, SYRACUSE.
>> MAYBE PETE WAS RIGHT BECAUSE
THERE CAN'T BE TOO MUCH GOING
ONNER THAT GOING TO REOPEN THE
CASE.
COME ON, SYRACUSE, YOU'RE BETTER
THAN THAT!
YOU GOT A SCHOOL OF JOURNALISM!
>> I WENT TO SYRACUSE, AND I
HAVE TO ADMIT, HE'S RIGHT.
THERE'S NOT A LOT TO DO.
IT'S ACOLLEGE TOWNWN BUT THEY
ARE -- THEY ARE PROVING HIS
POINT BECAUSE SYRACUSE D.A.
WILLIAM FITZPATRICK, HE MUST
HAVE BEEN WATCHING THAT VIDEO,
BY THE WAY, BECAUSE HE DOES WANT
TO REOPEN THE CASE.
SO HERE'S THE THING, PETE AND
HIS FRIEND, THEY WERE PULLED
OVER FOR -- IT WAS LIKE THEY
WERE FILMING THERE AND NERP
PULLED OVER AND HIS FRIEND WAS
TAKEN OVER AND CHARGED WITH
POSSESSION OF MARIJUANA.
PETE WAS NOT CHARGED.
HE EXPLAINED HE WOULD ASK POLICE
TO LOOK INTO THE CHARGES AND
THEN HE SAID, THEN WE WILL SEE
HOW MUCH HE REALLY LIKES
SYRACUSE.
SO HE'S NOT MAKING ANY FRIENDS
BY TIPPING THEM OFF.
>> TOM PETTY AND THE
HEARTBREAKERS.
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE PETE WAS
SWEATING IT BECAUSE HE WAS
SHOWING UP AND SHOWING OUT LAST
NIGHT.
HE WAS PARTYING WITH KANYE,
TIMOTHEE CHALAMET, ALL AT THE
CUB WHY YOU'S 53rd BIRTHDAY.
THEY WERE AT NOBU IN MALIBU,
HIGH-PROFILE SPOT AND VERY HARD
TO GET INTO.
I AM JUST SURPRISED TO SEE PETE
AND KANYE ALL BUDDY, BUDDY.
AS YOU REMEMBER, WHEN KANYE CAME
ON "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE" WITH
THE MAGA HAT ON, YOU KNOW, PETE
WAS NOT PLEASED ABOUT IT AT ALL.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, PETE THEN
WENT ON TO WEAR A MAKE KANYE
2006 AGAIN HAT, WHILE RIPPING
HIS PERFORMANCE.
SO, I MEAN --
>> THEN HE GOES TO MALIBU AND
GETS ALL HOLLYWOOD ON US.
>> ANYTHING FOR SUSHI.
>> HE CERTAINLY HAS A REASON TO
CELEBRATE BECAUSE IT WAS JUST
ANNOUNCED HE'S BEEN CAST IN A
NEW MOVIE DIRECTED BY JUDD
APATOW.
NOW, IT'S AN UNTITLED COMEDY
THAT HE ACTUALLY CO-WROTE, SO
IT'S GOING TO MIRROR HIS LIFE,
INCLUDING THE DEATH OF HIS
FATHER, WHO PASSED AWAY ON 9/11.
HIS FATHER WAS A FIREFIGHTER.
>> HE'S GOING TO BE DIGGING UP
HURTFUL STUFF.
>> AND HOPEFULLY FUNNY STUFF.
>> A LOT OF COMEDIANS BRING
THEIR OWN LIFE INTO COMEDY.
BUT IN SOME OTHER CASTING NEWS,
PRIYANKA CHOPRA JONAS, THAT'S
HER NAME NOW, SHE JUST REVEALED
SHE'S GOING TO STAR IN THE FILM
ADAPTATION OF IN THE HE NETFLIX
DOC "WILD WILD COUNTRY."
THCHS A HUGE PHENOMENON.
SHE'S GOING TO PLAY MA ATHAT
SHEILA, THE ASSISTANT TO THE
CULT LEADER.
SO THIS IS ACTUALLY A REALLY BIG
DEAL.
THAT WAS A HUGE -- A LOT OF BUZZ
ON NETFLIX.
>>> IN OTHER CASTING NEWS, BEN
AFFLECK IS HANGING UP HIS CAPE.
HE WILL NOT BE BATMAN, IT'S
OFFICIAL.
YOU KNOW GUYS, HE WAS ONCE SET
TO NOT ONLY STAR IN IT BUT ALSO
SUPPOSED TO DIRECT IT AS WELL.
BUT DEADLINE IS REPORTING THE
STUDIO IS LOOKING TO GO A LITTLE
YOUNGER, DARLING.
I CALL IT AGE I MEAN.
BEN IS ONLY 46, WHEN MICHAEL
KIETEN STARRED IN BATMAN, HE WAS
40.
SAME EXACT THING.
>> I DON'T THINK THIS IS BECAUSE
OF AGE THOUGH.
THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF PROBLEMS
WITH THIS.
YOU MENTIONED HE WAS ORIGINALLY
SUPPOSED TO DIRECT.
THAT WAS ACTUALLY TWO YEARS AGO
WHEN THAT NEWS CAME OUT.
THEN HE WAS TAKEN OFF FROM
DIRECTING.
NOW HE'S NOT STARRING.
D.C. THEY ARE RETOOLING AND
RESETTING A LOT OF THEIR
FRANCHISES.
I THINK THAT IS WHAT THIS IS
ALL.
NOT AGEISM.
>> I STILL WANT TO BE CAT WOMAN!
I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S D.C. OR
MARVEL.
>> BEVY FOR CAT WOMAN!
>>> STARS LIKE TRAVIS SCOTT AND
CARDI B GET READY TO ASCEND ON
THE CITY OF ATLANTA FOR SUPER
BOWL LIII, ATLANTA'S NATIVE T.I.
HAS A SET OF RULES A-LIST
VISITORS NEED FOLLOW WHEN THEY
LAND ON HIS HOME TURF.
LET ME TELL YOU WHAT THEY ARE.
HE POSTED 11 ATLANTA SUPER BOWL
RULES ON INSTAGRAM.
RULE NUMBER EIGHT, WE RESPECT
OUR HOMELESS.
PLEASE CALL THEM UNC OR AUNTIE
RESPECTIVELY AND ALSO DROP THEM
AN DOLLAR OR TWO.
I'M ADDING MY OWN RULES.
>> DO THAT.
>> RULE NUMBER 11, IF YOU DON'T
PAY YOUR STRIPPER, SHE WILL
FIGHT YOU.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THAT'S TRUE.
THOSE GIRLS WORK HARD FOR THE
MONEY!
AND ALL OF THEM BALLERS UP IN
ATLANTA, WHERE THE DOLLARS AT?
>> AND GUY STRIPPERS TOO.
THEY WORK HARD FOR THE MONDAY.
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT NO
GUY STRIPPERS.
>> RULE NUMBER, ANYBODY CAN SELL
YOU PARKING.
>> THAT GOES BAING TO WHAT HE
SAID ABOUT AUNTIE AND UNC.
THE HOMELESS PEOPLE WILL
DEFINITELY NOT ONLY SELL YOU
PARKING BUT ALSO GUIDE YOU INTO
YOUR PARKING SPOT.
BUT AFTER THEY DO THAT, YOU'VE
GOT TO PAY THEM WITH THAT MONEY.
>> RIGHT.
AUNT AND UNC GETTING PAID.
>> THERE YOU GO!
>>> DO WE KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH CARDI B AND OFFSET?
THAT'S ATLANTA.
WHAT'S THE LATEST.
>> HERE'S THE LATEST.
CARDI WAS IN COURT IN QUEENS,
NEW YORK, THIS MORNING, AND SO
HER ASSAULT CASE, THE ASSAULT
CASE WITH THE STRIPPERS AND
QUEEN --
>> IN THE STRIP CLUB.
ALL CONFUSING.
IT'S BEEN A JURNED UNTIL APRIL.
REPORTERS ARE ASKING QUESTIONS
BECAUSE THERE'S A STORY SHE AND
OFFSET ARE BACK TOGETHER.
THEY ASKED HER ABOUT IT AND SHE
SAID, WE'RE WORKING THINGS OUT,
BABY.
BUT SHE'S GIVING US MIXED
MESSAGES BECAUSE "TMZ" REPORTED
THEY'RE BACK TOGETHER AND SHE'S
MOVING BACK TO ATLANTA BACK INTO
THE HOME WITH OFFSET AND SHE
FIRED OFF A TWEET, "TMZ," WHY
YOU BE LYING?
I HAVEN'T EVEN BEEN IN ALT SINCE
CHRISTMAS.
AND THEN SHE DELETED IT.
>> CARDI B HAS BEEN HINTING SHE
WANTS TO GET BACK WITH OFFSET.
LAST WEEK SHE POSTED THIS
PICTURE OF OFFSET KITSCHING HER
DAUGHTER KULTURE AND HER CAPTION
WAS, I WANT TO GO HOME.
>> THAT IS SO SWEET.
I WILL TELL YOU THIS, IF CARDI
IS IN ATLANTA THIS WEEKEND,
SHE'S GOING TO MAKE ALL OF THE
MONEY.
AND IF SHE'S IN THE HOME WITH
OFFSET, I WOULD SAY YOU SHOULD
AIRBNB IT, DARLING, BECAUSE YOU
CAN MAKE SO MUCH MONEY THIS
WEEKEND.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
EVERYONE IS LOOKING FOR A PLACE
TO STAY IN ATLANTA.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> BUT IT'S EXPENSIVE.
>>> COMING UP, FIND OUT WHAT
BROUGHT CELINE DION TO TEARS AT
FASHION WEEK.
AND LATER, THE SURPRISING REASON
RYAN SEACREST KNOWS MORE ABOUT
THE STARS' LOVE LIVES THAN THE
REST OF US.
Could switching to GEICO
really save you
fifteen percent or more
on car insurance?
Did the little piggy cry
wee wee wee all the way home?
Weeeeeee, weeeeeee weeeeeee
weeeee weeeeeeee.
Max. (SIGH) ...MAXWELL!
Yeah?
You're home.
Oh, cool, thanks Mrs. A.
GEICO. Fifteen minutes
could save you
fifteen percent or more.
It's just a cough.
Yeah right.
And the earth is flat.
Ahhh!!
Treat your cough seriously
with Robitussin CF Max.
Nothing lasts longer
and treats more symptoms for
your cough, cold and flu.
Robitussin. Because
it's never just a cough.
Brushing only reaches
25% of your mouth.
LISTERINE® cleans
virtually 100%.
Helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%.
Always go for 100.
Bring Out the Bold™
When you shop with us, you
know how to score.
But did you know you could be
saving even more?
With the TJX rewards credit card
- every time you shop at
our stores,
you earn 5% back in rewards.
TJX Rewards credit card.
An even better value every day.
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
All new Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Pick your favorite stuffed
pasta, sauce and topping.
It's all never ending.
All new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "PAGE SIX
TV."
IT'S CELINE DION'S WORLD AND
WE'RE JUST LIVING IN IT.
YESTERDAY IT WAS ANNOUNCED A
FILM ABOUT HER LIFE CALLED "THE
POWER OF LOVE" IS IN THE WORKS
AND I'M SO EXCITED FOR THAT.
THIS WEEK SHE CRUSHED IT AT
PARIS FASHION WEEK.
LOOK AT HER HERE IN ARMANI.
SHE LOOKS AMAZING.
BUT IT WASN'T THAT LONG AGO SHE
STEPPED OUT LOOKING LIKE THIS
AND THIS AND THIS ON THE RED
CARPET.
I'M A HUGE CELINE FAN, BUT BEVY,
HOW DID SHE TRANSFORM TO
HOMEGROWN TO HAUTE COUTURE?
>> I WILL TELL YOU, IT'S BEEN AN
AMAZING TRANSFORMATION.
SHE RAMPED IT UP WHEN SHE
COLLABORATED WITH STYLIST TO THE
A-LIST, MR. LAROCHE.
AND SHE'S COME A LONG WAY, BABY.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT CELINE'S
LOOK FROM PARIS FASHION WEEK.
FIRST UP, WE HAVE THIS, A
SNEAKER $925.
CELLIO DRESS IS OLD OUT AND
THERE'S A HYBRID HERRINGBONE
SWEATER JACKET -- I LOVE ALL OF
THESE THINGS SEPARATELY,
SNEAKERS NOT SO MUCH, BUT ALL
TOGETHER NOT MY FAVORITE LOOK.
>> I THINK IT LOOKS GOOD.
>> YOU THINK IT LOOKS GOOD?
>> IT'S LIKE CASUAL COUTURE FOR
PARIS.
>> WHEN YOU'RE AN AVAUNT GUARD
FASHIONISTA, THERE ARE
OFTENTIMES YOU HAVE A MISS AND
THIS IS JUST ONE AND IT'S OKAY.
>> BEVY, I AGREE WITH YOU BUT I
THINK IF ANYONE BUT CELINE WORE
IT, IT WOULD HAVE BEEN A
DISASTER.
SHE MAKES IT LIKE NOT QUITE A
>> NEXT UP, THIS IS A JUMPSUIT.
DISASTER.
LOOK AT THE PLUNGING NECKLINE.
>> NEXT UP, THIS IS A JUMPSUIT.
EXAGGERATED 1980 SHOULDER PAD,
LOOK AT THE PLUNGING NECKLINE.
WHICH TRADITIONALLY PEOPLE LIKE
EXAGGERATED 1980 SHOULDER PAD,
TO WEAR BECAUSE IT MAKES YOUR
WHICH TRADITIONALLY PEOPLE LIKE
WAIST LOOK EVEN SMALLER, THEY
TO WEAR BECAUSE IT MAKES YOUR
CALL IT WASP WAIST.
WAIST LOOK EVEN SMALLER, THEY
BUT PEOPLE ARE COMMENTING ON
CALL IT WASP WAIST.
CELINE LOOKING INCREDIBLY THIN,
BUT PEOPLE ARE COMMENTING ON
KIND OF RAINING ON HER PARADE.
CELINE LOOKING INCREDIBLY THIN,
BUT CELINE HEARD THEM AND
KIND OF RAINING ON HER PARADE.
CLAPPED BY SAYING, IN THE SUN,
BUT CELINE HEARD THEM AND
DON'T BOTHER, DON'T TAKE A
CLAPPED BY SAYING, IN THE SUN,
PICTURE.
DON'T BOTHER, DON'T TAKE A
IF YOU LIKE IT, I'LL BE THERE.
PICTURE.
IF YOU DON'T, LEAVE ME ALONE.
IF YOU LIKE IT, I'LL BE THERE.
>> GOOD FOR HER!
IF YOU DON'T, LEAVE ME ALONE.
>> GOOD FOR HER.
>> GOOD FOR HER!
>> SHE LOOKS AMAZING.
>> GOOD FOR HER.
>> SHE DOES.
>> SHE LOOKS AMAZING.
I WOULD LIKE A LITTLE MORE MEAT
>> SHE DOES.
ON HER.
I WOULD LIKE A LITTLE MORE MEAT
BUD ANYWAY, NEXT, HEAD TO TOE
ON HER.
LEATHER, I LOVE THIS LOOK.
BUD ANYWAY, NEXT, HEAD TO TOE
MAROON LEATHER BLAZER AND MOST
LEATHER, I LOVE THIS LOOK.
IMPORTANT PART OF THIS LOOK IS
MAROON LEATHER BLAZER AND MOST
THOUGH IS HER TOY BOY!
IMPORTANT PART OF THIS LOOK IS
>> HER TOY BOY PEP WHY MUNOZ IS
THOUGH IS HER TOY BOY!
ONE OF HER DANCERS AS SHE SPOKE
>> HER TOY BOY PEP WHY MUNOZ IS
ABOUT HIM.
ONE OF HER DANCERS AS SHE SPOKE
YEAH, THERE'S ANOTHER MAN IN MY
ABOUT HIM.
LIFE BUT NOT THE MAN IN MY LIFE.
YEAH, THERE'S ANOTHER MAN IN MY
WE'RE FRIENDS, WE'RE BEST
LIFE BUT NOT THE MAN IN MY LIFE.
FRIENDS.
WE'RE FRIENDS, WE'RE BEST
BY THE WAY, WHEN I SAY I'M
FRIENDS.
SINGLE, PLEASE LEAVE ME ALONE.
BY THE WAY, WHEN I SAY I'M
>> I LOVE IT.
SINGLE, PLEASE LEAVE ME ALONE.
WELL NEXT UP WE HAVE A BAT
>> I LOVE IT.
SHEEBA 3-4 LOOK OF 2019.
WELL NEXT UP WE HAVE A BAT
I CALL THIS SOPHISTICATED
SHEEBA 3-4 LOOK OF 2019.
PRAIRIE CHIC.
I CALL THIS SOPHISTICATED
GREEN VELVET JACKET, BROACH, I
PRAIRIE CHIC.
THINK SHE LOOKS DIVINE.
GREEN VELVET JACKET, BROACH, I
THIS NEXT LOOK, CLASSIC
THINK SHE LOOKS DIVINE.
VALENTINO.
THIS NEXT LOOK, CLASSIC
IT'S A MONO CHROMATIC
VALENTINO.
MASTERPIECE, DARLING!
IT'S A MONO CHROMATIC
LOOK AT THAT.
MASTERPIECE, DARLING!
YOU NEVER KNEW IT COULD LOOK SO
LOOK AT THAT.
GOOD.
YOU NEVER KNEW IT COULD LOOK SO
>> IT ACTUALLY BROUGHT HER TO
GOOD.
TEARS BUT IT WASN'T BECAUSE OF
>> IT ACTUALLY BROUGHT HER TO
THE VALENTINO'S FASHION.
TEARS BUT IT WASN'T BECAUSE OF
IT WAS THE SONG PLAYING "FIRST
THE VALENTINO'S FASHION.
TIME I EVER SAW YOUR FACE" AND
IT WAS THE SONG PLAYING "FIRST
IT WAS HER WEDDING THAT SONG
TIME I EVER SAW YOUR FACE" AND
THAT MADE HER THINK OF HER
IT WAS HER WEDDING THAT SONG
EX-HUSBAND -- LATE HUSBAND,
THAT MADE HER THINK OF HER
RENEE.
EX-HUSBAND -- LATE HUSBAND,
>> THAT'S SAD.
RENEE.
ABOUT UT AT LEAST SHE LOOKED
>> THAT'S SAD.
GOOD CRYING.
ABOUT UT AT LEAST SHE LOOKED
I KNOW YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT WAS
GOOD CRYING.
THE PARIS FASHION WEEK OUTFIT
I KNOW YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT WAS
THAT SLAYED THE WORLD, THAT
THE PARIS FASHION WEEK OUTFIT
CELINE CAME TO SLAY?
THAT SLAYED THE WORLD, THAT
I WILL TELL YOU LATER IN THE
CELINE CAME TO SLAY?
SHOW.
I WILL TELL YOU LATER IN THE
>>> COMING UP, JARED GOFF MAY BE
SHOW.
DATING THIS MODEL AND A
>>> COMING UP, JARED GOFF MAY BE
SURPRISING RYAN SEACREST
DATING THIS MODEL AND A
CONNECTION.
SURPRISING RYAN SEACREST
I'LL EXPLAIN IT ALL RIGHT AFTER
CONNECTION.
THIS.
A migraine hope
To be there...
for the good.
And not so good.
For the mundane.
The awe-inspiring.
The heart racing.
The heart breaking.
That's what life is all about...
showing up.
Unless migraine steals your
chance  to say "I am here."
That's why, we created Aimovig..
A preventive treatment for
migraine in adults.
One dose, once a month.
Aimovig is proven to reduce
the number  of
monthly migraine days.
For some, that number can
be cut in half or more.
The most common side effects
are pain, redness,
or swelling at the injection
site and constipation.
These are your days
What will each one bring?
Doesn't matter,
as long as you can say...
"I am here."
Talk to your doctor about
preventing migraine
with Aimovig.
And be there more.
I switched to stimulant-free
MiraLAX for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives
forcefully stimulate
the nerves in
your colon.
MiraLAX is
different.
It works with
the water
in your body
to unblock
your system
naturally.
And it doesn't cause
harsh side effects.
That's why I choose MiraLAX.
Look for the pink cap.
>>> "PAGE SIX TV" NOW --
JULIANNE MOORE AND MARISSA
TOMORROW MAY DO WAY BACK TO HIGH
SCHOOL BUT JUST DISCOVERED THEY
MIGHT BE
When I believe in something,
I'm all in.
So if I'm gonna be blonde,
it's got to be great.
Superior Preference hair color
from L'Oreal.
Translucent, liquid gel formula.
Luminous, fade defying color
that lasts.
With incredible dimension-
incredible life.
Preference from L'Oreal Paris.
52 fade-defying shades
that last.
I own this blonde,
and I'm worth it.
Don't let cracked skin tell you
what to wear.
New AVEENO® Cracked Skin
CICA Ointment.
With Shea Butter and
Triple Oat Complex.
For fast relief and a protective
barrier for lasting relief.
Wear what you love,
AVEENO®.
TV."
WE KNOW THE PATRIOTS WILL HAVE
PRESENTSY OF SUPERMODELS THIS
SUNDAY.
GISELE WILL BE CHEERING ON TOM
BRADY AND WE TALKED ABOUT
GRONK'S MODEL GIRLFRIEND KAMIL
CAUSTIC BEFORE BUT IT'S TIME TO
LEARN ABOUT THE RAMS' PLAYERS
WIVES AND GIRLFRIENDS IN A
SPECIAL EDITION OF --
>> WIGGLE WIGGLE, WIG!
>> I HAVE MY OWN JINGLE NOW!
I LIKE THAT!
THE RAMS HAVEN'T BEEN BACK IN
L.A. VERY LONG BUT THEY'VE
DEFINITELY GONE HOLLYWOOD.
OFFENSIVE LINEMAN AND HIS WYCHE
ASIA EVEN BRIEFLY STARTED IN
THEE REALITY SHOW "HOLLYWOOD AND
FOOTBALL.
NOW JARED GOFF, THE RAMS
24-YEAR-OLD SUPERSTAR
QUARTERBACK IN THE RUMOR MILL IS
THAT HE'S NOW DATING MODEL
KRISTIN HARPER.
THE RUMOR STARTED WHEN THE SITE
REPORTED THE TWO WERE A COUPLE
AND SHE WAS SPOTTED IN THE
STANDS AT ONE OF HIS RECENT
GAMES BUT IF YOU LOOK ON
INSTAGRAM, THIS IS HOW WE KNOW
IT'S A REAL THING, THEY FOLLOW
EACH OTHER.
IT'S A BIG DEAL IN 2019.
THE CRAZY THING ABOUT THIS STORY
IS THERE'S A RYAN SEACREST
CONNECTION.
I LOVE THIS.
JARED GOFF'S ROOMMATE, SHE WORKS
IN THE SAME BUILDING THAT THE
RADIO SHOW ON AIR WITH RYAN
SEACREST AIRS FROM.
SO RYAN ON AIR WITH RYAN
SEACREST HAD PATRICK HENRY ON
THE SHOW TO TALK ABOUT THE SUPER
BOWL AND SNEAKY SEACREST, HE
SLIPPED IN SOME QUESTIONS ABOUT
JARED'S LOVE LIFE.
WATCH THIS.
>> NOW, HE DOES HAVE A
GIRLFRIEND?
>> I'M NOT GOING TO ANSWER ANY
PERSONAL QUESTIONS!
>> THIS GUY IS INVOLVED!
>> WE KNOW YOU FOLLOW A GIRL
NAMED KRISTIN.
>> YEAH.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> RYAN SEACREST INVESTIGATIVE
REPORTER.
>> I LOVE IT.
>> HE HAS CHOPS.
I SAY KUDOS TO YOUNG PATRICK TO
NOT GIVING ANYTHING UP.
THAT'S HOW YOU GET KICKED OUT OF
THE FRIENDS CIRCLE.
>> I LOVE WHAT YOU SAID ABOUT
RYAN, IF RYAN CAN PROD INTO
PEOPLE'S LOVE LIVES, SO CAN WE,
RIGHT?
FANS ARE ALSO FASCINATED BY
RAMS' COACH SEAN MCVAY'S
RELATIONSHIP WITH THE MODEL
VERONICA HUMMAND.
SEAN IS THE YOUNGEST HELD COACH
HIRED IN THE NFL, HE'S ONLY 43.
THAT'S VERY YOUNG.
>> TASTY.
>> VERONICA IS A 29-YEAR-OLD
MODEL FROM UKRAINE AND WENT TO
GEORGE MASON UNIVERSITY.
I KNOW NOTHING ABOUT SEAN MCVAY
BUT WHAT I LOVE IS VERONICA
CALLS HIM SEAN McBAY.
>> THAT IS VERY CUTE.
>>> COMING UP CHRIS BROWN, NAOMI
CAMPBELL AND JONAH HILL WERE
SHOWING OUT IN PARIS BUT BEVY
WILL FINALLY REVEAL THE LIST
THAT MADE US ALL SAFE UP NEXT.
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
The cold and flu fighting
machine.
You put in your machine.
Press the button to brew up
powerful relief.
To defeat your toughest
cold and flu symptoms fast.
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
Press. Sip. Relief.
You've tried moisturizer
after moisturizer
but one blows them
all out of the water.
Hydro Boost
from Neutrogena®.
With hyaluronic acid
to plump skin cells
so it bounces back.
Neutrogena®
I had been diagnosed with
Stage 4 prostate cancer.
I serve in the general
assembly and we work
together across the aisle
to get things done.
And that's the way
it is at CTCA.
What Fred needed was
a management team.
Not just to have a
long-term strategy for
quantity of life, but
also an active strategy
for quality of life.
My PSA is under control.
CTCA gave me an
opportunity to accomplish
my goals and my dreams.
Learn more at
cancercenter.com/philadelphia
Appointments available now.
You can't put a price on love.
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
Brushing only reaches
25% of your mouth.
LISTERINE® cleans
virtually 100%.
Helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%.
Always go for 100.
Bring Out the Bold™
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "PAGE SIX
TV."
WE'RE LIVE, LOVERS!
I TOOK YOU ON THE TOUR WITH
CELINE DION PARIS FASHION WEEK
EXTRAVAGANZA WHERE SHE STOLE THE
SHOW AND I SAVED THE BEST FOR
LAST.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS OSCAR de la RENTA.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> DARLING, IT RETAILS FOR
$3,490.
THIS LOOK GIVES ME MY ENTIRE
LIFE.
IT'S SCARLET, DARLING, YOU KNOW
I LOVE SCARLET, AND THIS IS
ABSOLUTELY SHOWING OFF SHE'S
LIVING HER BEST LIFE.
>> SHE DEFINITELY IS.
WE HAVE TO GIVE A SHOUT OUT TO
DERRICK AND HANNAH JETER.
"PAGE SIX" SAID THEY WELCOMED
THEIR 1EKD DAUGHTER.
THAT'S AWE SM.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> OTHER BIG NEWS IS IT'S JUSTIN
TIMBERLAKE'S BIRTHDAY.
>> GET TO THE REAL STORY!
>> J.T. HAPPENS TO SHARE A
BIRTHDAY WITH MY MOM!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, MOM!
>> THE GRAND DAMME!
>>> STAY UP TO DATE WITH ALL OF
THE BREAKING STORIES.
GO TO PAGESIX.COM.
REMEMBER, IF YOU DON'T WANT IT
ON "PAGE SIX," DON'T DO IT!
>> SEE YOU NEXT TIME.
Switch to Fios and get
entertainment delivered
to your home like no one else.
Because Fios is a 100%
fiber-optic network.
That means you'll get the
fastest internet available
and Fios TV One with amazing
4K capability,
and an advanced voice remote.
And now we'll give you a Netflix
premium plan for a full year.
So you can stream your favorite
Netflix shows
and movies in 4K on 4
devices at once.
Already have Netflix?
We'll cover the cost for one
year.
Just switch for 79.99 a month
with a two-year agreement
and get Fios Gigabit Connection
with TV and phone
with a 2-year price guarantee.
And not only will you get a
Netflix premium plan on us for a
year,
you'll be able to find Netflix
in the Fios Channel guide
and use the advanced voice
remote to launch Netflix
and easily find all the
channels,movies and shows
you love.
When you think about it,
there are so many entertaining
reasons to switch to Fios.
100% fiber-optic network.
100% phenomenal.
Go to getfios.com today.
When you shop with us, you
know how to score.
But did you know you could be
saving even more?
With the TJX rewards credit card
- every time you shop at
our stores,
you earn 5% back in rewards.
TJX Rewards credit card.
An even better value every day.