>>> COMING UP RIGHT NOW ON "PAGE
SIX TV" -- IT'S MASS FINGER
MANIA, WHEN JENNY McCARTHY
CONFIDED TO US ABOUT THE
SURPRISE HIT.
>>> IT'S "WAY TO GO WEDNESDAY,"
FROM TIM KAY TO COMMON, WE'RE
SHOUTING OUT CELEBRITIES FOR
DOING GREAT THINGS.
PLUS, MICHAEL B. JORDAN DOES
SOMETHING NOBODY'S EVER DONE
BEFORE.
AND BEVY TALKS TO CLIVE DAVIS,
WHAT HE TOLD US ABOUT CARDI B
AND GREAT LATE WHITNEY HOUSTON.
>>> FIRST, J LAW ARE ABOUT TO
MEET THE IN-LAWS, AS SHE AND
COOKE ARE ENGAGED.
ED HEARD IT HERE FIRST.
SHE WAS ROCKING A MASSIVE RING
WHILE THEE DINED AT A HOT SPOT.
NOW WE KNOW THE KNEE R NEW SHE'S
ONLY BEEN SHARING WITH HER
CLOSEST FRIENDS.
REPS OFFICIALLY CONFIRMED TO US
SHE'S TYING THE KNOT.
THAT'S TODAY'S TOP STORIES.
THERE'S MORE "PAGE SIX TV"
STARTING RIGHT NOW.
>> WELCOME TO "PAGE SIX TV."
I'M BEVY SMITH AND CARLOS IS
HERE AND THE WEB MEISTER.
THE MATH SINGER QUICKLY HAS
BECOME MUCH-WATCH TV FOR
MILLIONS OF VIEWERS EVERY
WEDNESDAY BUT AT ONE POINT ONLY
ONE PERSON CAN BELIEVE IN THE
PHENOM AND THAT WOULD BE JENNY
McCARTHY.
ELIZABETH, HOW THE HECK DOES
JENNY McCARTHY KNOW SOMETHING
NONE OF US KNEW?
>> SHE'S A SMART COOKIE.
WE CAUGHT UP WITH HER IN
ATLANTA, WHERE SHE WAS THERE FOR
THE SUPER BOWL AND SHE'S ONE OF
THE PANELISTS ON "THE MASKED
SINGER."
SO SHE'S TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT CELEBRITY IS UNDER THE
COSTUMES.
SHE SAID, MY AGENTS WILL BE MAD
AT ME FOR SAYING THIS, BUT WE
HAVE A FEW PROJECTS YOU OFFERED
FOR.
TAKE A LOOK BUT DON'T LUKE AT
THIS ONE, YOU'RE GOING TO HATE
IT.
SHE SAID NO, LET ME TAKE A LOOK.
SHE WATCHED THE KOREAN VERSION
BECAUSE THE MASKED SINGER IS
BASED ON KRIEN FORMAT.
SHE SAID IT'S WEIRD AND
DIFFERENT AND IT WILL GET
PEOPLE'S ATTENTION.
SHE WAS RIGHT ABOUT THIS, MY
AGENTS CALLED ME AND THEY'RE THE
ONLY ONE WHO BELIEVED IN THE
SHOW.
EVERY SINGLE PERSON OUTSIDE OF
THE NETWORK THOUGHT THOFS THE
WORSE THING TO POSSIBLY COME ON
TELEVISION.
HERE'S WHAT I WANT TO SAY,
FIRST, IDEAS OUT OF THE BOX IS
WHAT WORKS BECAUSE THERE'S SO
MUCH CONTENT.
AND THIS IS BASED ON A HUGE HIT
OVERSEAS SO OF COURSE JENNY
McKOORJY BELIEVED IN IT.
>> YOU KNOW, WHAT THE WACKIER
THE BETTER.
WITH SO MUCH CON 2E79, YOU NEED
SOMETHING TO STAND OUT.
>> IT'S HUGE, EVERYBODY'S
WATCHING.
I BELIEVE IT'S NUMBER ONE SHOW
AT THE MOMENT.
TOMMY CHONG WAS THE PINEAPPLE,
TERRY BRADSHAW WAS THE DEER,
MARGARET CHO WAS THE POODLE AND
TORI SPELLING -- I DIDN'T SEE
THIS ONE, TORI SPELLING WAS
REVEALED AS THE UNICORN LAST
WEEK.
PEOPLE ARE STILL GUESSING.
PEOPLE THINK -- I'M SURE YOU
KNOW NICK CANNON, HE'S THE HOST,
SO HE PROBABLY KNOWS IT ALL.
>> I THINK NICK CANNON DOES
KNOW.
HE WEARS THOSE TURBANS.
HE REMINDS ME OF THE JOHNNY
CARSON CHARACTER, CON KNACK THE
MAGNIFICENT.
THESE LIKE CON-YAK THE
>>> PEOPLE THINK GLADYS KNIGHT
MAGNIFICENT.
MAY BE THE B AND LA TOYA JACKSON
>>> PEOPLE THINK GLADYS KNIGHT
MAY BE THE ALIEN.
MAY BE THE B AND LA TOYA JACKSON
WE WILL SEE WHO GETS UNMASKED
MAY BE THE ALIEN.
TONIGHT.
WE WILL SEE WHO GETS UNMASKED
>> IF THE ALIEN CAN'T SING, IT'S
TONIGHT.
DEFINITELY LA TOYA JACKSON.
>> IF THE ALIEN CAN'T SING, IT'S
>>> WE HAVE THE LATEST TWIST IN
DEFINITELY LA TOYA JACKSON.
ROBERT DE NIRO'S DIVORCE.
>>> WE HAVE THE LATEST TWIST IN
HE AND HIGHTOWER ARE DUE BACK IN
ROBERT DE NIRO'S DIVORCE.
COURT TOMORROW AND SOURCES CLOSE
HE AND HIGHTOWER ARE DUE BACK IN
TO DE NIRO SAID GRACE IS THE ONE
COURT TOMORROW AND SOURCES CLOSE
WHO WANTS THE PROCEEDINGS TO BE
TO DE NIRO SAID GRACE IS THE ONE
PUBLIC.
WHO WANTS THE PROCEEDINGS TO BE
AS WE ALL KNOW, ROBERT DE NIRO
PUBLIC.
IS ONE OF THE MOST NOTORIOUSLY
AS WE ALL KNOW, ROBERT DE NIRO
PRIVATE CELEBS.
IS ONE OF THE MOST NOTORIOUSLY
WHEN HE FILED FOR DIVORCE, HE
PRIVATE CELEBS.
FILED ANONYMOUS VERSE AS NONE
WHEN HE FILED FOR DIVORCE, HE
MUSS.
FILED ANONYMOUS VERSE AS NONE
"PAGE SIX" FIGURED OUT IT WAS
MUSS.
HIM AND HIGHTOWER.
"PAGE SIX" FIGURED OUT IT WAS
BUT NOW SOURCES ARE TELLING US
HIM AND HIGHTOWER.
THIS COULD HAVE BEEN RESOLVED
BUT NOW SOURCES ARE TELLING US
PRIVATELY BUT GRACE IS THE ONE
THIS COULD HAVE BEEN RESOLVED
WHO WANTS IT TO BE PUBLIC, SHE
PRIVATELY BUT GRACE IS THE ONE
WANTS TO DRAG DID OUT.
WHO WANTS IT TO BE PUBLIC, SHE
THAT'S WHAT ONE SOURCE IS
WANTS TO DRAG DID OUT.
TELLING US.
THAT'S WHAT ONE SOURCE IS
YOU CAN SEE, WE'VE HAD REPORTERS
TELLING US.
OUT AT THE COURTHOUSE AND YOU
YOU CAN SEE, WE'VE HAD REPORTERS
CAN SEE HOW UNCOMFORTABLE RONT
OUT AT THE COURTHOUSE AND YOU
DE NIRO IS THAT THIS IS SO
CAN SEE HOW UNCOMFORTABLE RONT
PUBLIC.
DE NIRO IS THAT THIS IS SO
IN FACT, TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
PUBLIC.
>> SO I'M A YOUNG GIRL, NOT
IN FACT, TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
SMART --
>> SO I'M A YOUNG GIRL, NOT
>> NO, I DON'T THINK YOU ARE.
SMART --
YOU SOUND LIKE YOU'RE SMART BUT
>> NO, I DON'T THINK YOU ARE.
YOU'RE NOT.
YOU SOUND LIKE YOU'RE SMART BUT
>> WHY AM I NOT SNART.
YOU'RE NOT.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT SMART
>> WHY AM I NOT SNART.
DOING A JOB LIKE THIS.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT SMART
>> YOU CAN SEE HE'S CHASTISING A
DOING A JOB LIKE THIS.
REPORTER.
>> YOU CAN SEE HE'S CHASTISING A
BUT BOTH SIDES HAVE DIFFERENT
REPORTER.
TAKES.
BUT BOTH SIDES HAVE DIFFERENT
A LONGTIME DENORIO ASSOCIATE
TAKES.
TOLD US HE JUST WANTS TO SEE HIS
A LONGTIME DENORIO ASSOCIATE
KID.
TOLD US HE JUST WANTS TO SEE HIS
THE MONEY IS NOT AN ISSUE.
KID.
HE'S 75 YEARS OLD.
THE MONEY IS NOT AN ISSUE.
WITH A 20-YEAR-OLD AND THEY HAVE
HE'S 75 YEARS OLD.
A 7-YEAR-OLD, I BELIEVE.
WITH A 20-YEAR-OLD AND THEY HAVE
SO HE WANTS TO SEE HIS KID.
A 7-YEAR-OLD, I BELIEVE.
HE DOESN'T CARE ABOUT THE MONEY,
SO HE WANTS TO SEE HIS KID.
75 YEARS OLD.
HE DOESN'T CARE ABOUT THE MONEY,
BUT ANOTHER SOURCE CLOSE TO
75 YEARS OLD.
GRACE, BOB IS THE ONE FORCING
BUT ANOTHER SOURCE CLOSE TO
THIS PUBLIC AND ANOTHER SOURCE
GRACE, BOB IS THE ONE FORCING
SAID SHE WILL WIND UP GETTING
THIS PUBLIC AND ANOTHER SOURCE
LESS MONEY BECAUSE SHE'S
SAID SHE WILL WIND UP GETTING
HANDLING THIS IN THE COURTS
LESS MONEY BECAUSE SHE'S
PUBLICLY.
HANDLING THIS IN THE COURTS
SO WE WILL SEE.
PUBLICLY.
>> I'M BEVY AND I STAND BY HER.
SO WE WILL SEE.
>> IT'S IMPORTANT TO NOTE THAT
>> I'M BEVY AND I STAND BY HER.
THERE'S A PRENUP, SO THEY'RE NOT
>> IT'S IMPORTANT TO NOTE THAT
GOING TO DISCUSS IT PUBLICLY.
THERE'S A PRENUP, SO THEY'RE NOT
DISCUSS THAT PART OF IT.
GOING TO DISCUSS IT PUBLICLY.
>>> THE GRAMMYS ARE SUNDAY.
DISCUSS THAT PART OF IT.
BEVY, YOU JUST HUNG OUT WITH THE
>>> THE GRAMMYS ARE SUNDAY.
MOST IMPORTANT MAN THE WEEKEND,
BEVY, YOU JUST HUNG OUT WITH THE
CLIVE DAVIS.
MOST IMPORTANT MAN THE WEEKEND,
>> I DID.
CLIVE DAVIS.
THE GOLDEN ERA CLIVE DAVIS WAS
>> I DID.
ON MY SHOW "BEVELATIONS" ON
THE GOLDEN ERA CLIVE DAVIS WAS
SIRIUS XM.
ON MY SHOW "BEVELATIONS" ON
WE TALKED ABOUT THE RISE OF
SIRIUS XM.
CARDI B.
WE TALKED ABOUT THE RISE OF
HE TALKED ABOUT HOW SHE ATTENDED
CARDI B.
HIS GRAMMY PARTY LAST YEAR,
HE TALKED ABOUT HOW SHE ATTENDED
WHICH WAS HELD IN NEW YORK CITY,
HIS GRAMMY PARTY LAST YEAR,
ALL OF THE CAMERAS WERE AND HER.
WHICH WAS HELD IN NEW YORK CITY,
NOT BECAUSE SHE WAS THE BIGGEST
ALL OF THE CAMERAS WERE AND HER.
STAR IN THE ROOM, JUST BECAUSE
NOT BECAUSE SHE WAS THE BIGGEST
SHE WAS SO CAPTIVATING.
STAR IN THE ROOM, JUST BECAUSE
HE ALSO SAID HE REALLY LOVES THE
SHE WAS SO CAPTIVATING.
FACT SHE KNOWS MUSIC, SHE LOVES
HE ALSO SAID HE REALLY LOVES THE
MUSIC AND SHE CLEARLY WANTS TO
FACT SHE KNOWS MUSIC, SHE LOVES
BE A PART OF THIS INDUSTRY AND
MUSIC AND SHE CLEARLY WANTS TO
SO SHE DRAWS PEOPLE IN.
BE A PART OF THIS INDUSTRY AND
I'M A BIG FAN OF HERS, OF
SO SHE DRAWS PEOPLE IN.
COURSE.
I'M A BIG FAN OF HERS, OF
WE ALSO TALKED ABOUT WHITNEY
COURSE.
HOUSTON.
WE ALSO TALKED ABOUT WHITNEY
OF COURSE, HE WAS VERY
HOUSTON.
INSTRUMENTAL IN HER CAREER, BUT
OF COURSE, HE WAS VERY
HE BROUGHT UP THE LAST TWO
INSTRUMENTAL IN HER CAREER, BUT
DOCUMENTARIES THAT WERE DONE ON
HE BROUGHT UP THE LAST TWO
HER ACTUALLY MADE HIM VERY SAD.
DOCUMENTARIES THAT WERE DONE ON
LET'S TAKE A LISTEN.
HER ACTUALLY MADE HIM VERY SAD.
>> SAD FOR ME THAT THE TWO
LET'S TAKE A LISTEN.
DOCUMENTARIES ON WHITNEY ONLY
>> SAD FOR ME THAT THE TWO
CONCENTRATED ON DRUG ADIRECTION,
DOCUMENTARIES ON WHITNEY ONLY
ON THE BAD MARRIAGE.
CONCENTRATED ON DRUG ADIRECTION,
AND YES, SHE DID HAVE THAT BUT
ON THE BAD MARRIAGE.
IT DID NOT CAPTURE THE OTHER
AND YES, SHE DID HAVE THAT BUT
SIDE OF WHITNEY.
IT DID NOT CAPTURE THE OTHER
>> I AGREE, IT DIDN'T CAPTURE
SIDE OF WHITNEY.
HER TALENT AND HER SKILL, RIGHT?
>> I AGREE, IT DIDN'T CAPTURE
BUT HE SAID WHEN THE BIOPIC DOES
HER TALENT AND HER SKILL, RIGHT?
COME OUT, THAT HE REALLY HOPES
BUT HE SAID WHEN THE BIOPIC DOES
THEY TELL ALL.
COME OUT, THAT HE REALLY HOPES
BUT THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT HE TO
THEY TELL ALL.
SAY.
BUT THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT HE TO
HE SAID, THE LEGAL POWER OF
SAY.
DRUGS SILENCE VIBRANT WOMEN.
HE SAID, THE LEGAL POWER OF
HE SAID THERE SHOULD BE A
DRUGS SILENCE VIBRANT WOMEN.
TELLALL, BUT HE ALSO HOPES THE
HE SAID THERE SHOULD BE A
BIOPIC CONVEYS HOW MAGNIFICENT
TELLALL, BUT HE ALSO HOPES THE
OF AN ARTIST SHE WAS.
BIOPIC CONVEYS HOW MAGNIFICENT
SHE WAS THE CONSUMMATE ARTIST
OF AN ARTIST SHE WAS.
AND ONE OF THE GREATEST OF ALL
SHE WAS THE CONSUMMATE ARTIST
TIME.
AND ONE OF THE GREATEST OF ALL
>> ABSOLUTELY.
TIME.
>> GOING DOWN IN HISTORY, RIGHT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I AGREE WITH HIM.
THAT WAS A GREAT INTERVIEW,
BEVY.
>>> IT'S CARLOS' FAVORITE DAY OF
THE WEEK, IT'S "WAY TO GO
WEDNESDAY."
SO WE'RE STARTING OUT BY SAYING
"WAY TO GO WEDNESDAY" TO SEE YA
TO GET PIZZA HUT TO HELP FEED
THE HOMELESS.
SHE TWEETED IS HEY, PIZZA HUT,
WOULD YOU CONSIDER DONATING A
PIZZA TO THE HOMELESS EVERY
NIGHT THIS WEEK?
AN HOUR AFTERWARDS BEEIA HUT
AGREED, WHICH IS AMAZING.
THE HASHTAG FEED THE HEART
ENCOURAGES HER FANS TO HELP THE
HOMELESS IN THEIR OWN COMMUNITY.
WAY TO GO.
I LOVE SHE'S PAYING IT FORWARD.
>>> AND WE'LL HAVE MORE GREAT
STORIES ABOUT HOW STARS LIKE KIM
KARDASHIAN AND COMMON ARE GIVING
BACK IN JUST A LITTLE BIT.
BUT TODAY'S NOT JUST ABOUT
SHINING A LIGHT ON STARS.
WE ALSO NEED TO SAY WAY TO GO TO
EVERYDAY PEOPLE LIKE CHICAGO
REAL ESTATE DEVELOPER CANDACE
PAYNE.
I LOVE THIS STORY.
SHE'S A DEVELOPER AND SHE HELPED
ORGANIZE PEOPLE TO GET HOTEL
ROOMS FOR THE HOMELESS DURING
THE POLAR VORTEX IN CHICAGO.
YOU KNOW THE WIND CHILLED FACTOR
I BELIEVE WAS LIKE NEGATIVE 39.
IT WAS BONECHILLING AND
FREEZING.
SEVERAL HOTELS ACTUALLY TURNED
HER DOWN BUT SHE DID NOT GIVE
UP.
IN FACT, SHE WAS ABLE TO
CONVINCE THE AMBER INN IN
BRONXVILLE TO OPEN.
SHE PAID FOR SOME OF THE HOTEL
ROOMS BUT OTHER PEOPLE HELPED
PAY FOR HOTEL ROOMS TOO SO
HOMELESS PEOPLE HAD A PLACE TO
STAY.
WAY TO GO.
>> THE BEST THING ABOUT THIS IS
SHE WAS JUST AN ORDINARY PEOPLE
WHO SAW PEOPLE SUFFERING AND
WANTED TO TAKE ACTION.
SHE SAID, WHAT INSPIRED ME WAS
MY CURRENT BLESSINGS SO I WAS
JUST TRYING TO GIVE BACK.
WAY TO GO, CANDACE!
>> AND THERE ARE SEVERAL HOTELS
WHO TURNED HER DOWN BECAUSE THEY
DIDN'T WANT THEIR HOTELS PACKED
WITH HOMELESS PEOPLE.
AND IT WAS COLD.
>> FREEZING, YES.
>>> WE WANT TO HEAR ABOUT THE
CANDACE FROM YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD.
HIT US UP ON SOCIAL MEDIA RIGHT
NOW WITH THE #WTGW AND LET US
KNOW WHO ELSE DESERVES A "WAY TO
GO WEDNESDAY" SHOUT-OUT.
WE WILL BE DOING MORE IN A
COUPLE OF MINUTES.
>>> MOVING ON, MEGHAN TRAINOR'S
HIGHLY ANTICIPATED THIRD ALBUM
CALLED "TREAT MYSELF" WAS
SUPPOSED TO DEBUT IN AUGUST BUT
IT GOT DELAYED.
THEN IT WAS SUPPOSED TO JOP
JANUARY 26th BUT THAT DATE CAME
AND WENT.
NOW SHE ADMITTED IT WILL NOT BE
COMING OUT FOR A VERY LONG TIME
BUT FOR A GOOD REASON.
SHE CAN'T STOP WRITING SONGS AND
SHE NEEDS TO GET THEM OUT OF HER
HEAD BEFORE SHE FINISHES THE AIL
BUNL.
SHE ALSO GOT MARRIED.
>> GOOD FOR HER!
>> SHE SAID GOING TO PUT OUT
MUSIC, THIS IS WHAT SHE JUST
REVEALED, SHE'S RELEASING A
SIX-SONG EP AND I LOVE WHAT IT'S
CALLED "THE LOVE TRAIN."
>> OH, I LOVE THAT.
HOPEFULLY WE CAN GET ON THE LOVE
TRAIN, HOPEFULLY IT COMES INTO
THE STATION AND IS NOT DELAYED
LIKE ALL OF THE REST OF THE
TRAINS.
>> SHE SAID THE SIX-SONG EP IS
COMING OUT FRIDAY.
>> WE'LL SEE.
I'M A COMMUTER.
I'LL BE WAITING FOR IT, BABY.
>> SHE HAS A HUGE FAN BASE.
I'M SURE PEOPLE ARE LOOKING
FORWARD TO "THE LOVE TRAIN" ON
FRIDAY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>>> STRUGGLING TO GET A NEW AIL
BULL OUT, WE'LL HAVE THE LATEST
ON THAT AND OUR SIX LIST OF
INTIMATE, LONG-LOST ALBUMS THAT
MAY NEVER SEE THE LIGHT OF DAY.
>>> FIRST, THE CHARITABLE KIM
KARDASHIAN IS IN NEW YORK FOR A
VERY G FOR A
VERY GOOD REASON.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHY RIGHT AFTER
THIS.
I switched to stimulant-free
MiraLAX for my constipation.
Stimulant laxatives
forcefully stimulate
the nerves in
your colon.
MiraLAX is
different.
It works with
the water
in your body
to unblock
your system
naturally.
And it doesn't cause
harsh side effects.
That's why I choose MiraLAX.
Look for the pink cap.
♪♪
♪ 'Cos I know what it means ♪
♪ To walk along the lonely
street of dreams ♪
♪ Here I go again on my--- ♪
You realize your vows are a
Whitesnake song?
I do.
If you ride, you get it.
GEICO Motorcycle.
15 minutes
could save you 15% or more.
(Thunderclap)
If your day doesn't
unfold as predicted.
Unfold this.
New Neutrogena®
Makeup Remover single.
And remove 99% of makeup.
100% rain or shine.
Neutrogena®.
I know it's hard Maddie.
But I promise,
it's gonna get better.
♪ ♪
(mom giggles)
TV."
KIM KARDASHIAN IS IN NEW YORK
FOR A VERY GOOD CAUSE, WHICH IS
PERFECT TIMING BECAUSE IT'S "WAY
TO GO WEDNESDAY."
KIM'S NEW YORK STAR-STUDDED
GALA IS TONIGHT AT THE BLACK TIE
EVENT HONORING THOSE WHO MADE
OUTSTANDING CONTRIBUTIONS TO THE
FIGHT AGAINST HIV AND AIDS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> SUCH AN IMPORTANT EVENT.
AND IT'S ALWAYS STAR-STUDDED, OF
COURSE.
SO KIM KARDASHIAN IS ONE OF THE
PRESENTERS TONIGHT, AND SOME OF
THE HONOREES INCLUDE FASHION
PHOTOGRAPHER MART OTHER MARCUS.
THEY JUST DID KENDALL JENNER'S
"VOGUE" ITALY PHOTO.
>> THEY SHOOT EVERYONE.
>> EVERYONE.
THEY WILL BE HONORED.
ANOTHER ACT IS BEING HONORED IS
MILLA JOVOVICH.
SHE'S ENTRENCHED WITH MULTIPLE
CHARITY THAT'S GIVE TO AIDS,
INCLUDING AIDS LIEFB AND THE
ELTON JOHN AIDS FOUNDATION.
AND I WILL BE THERE.
SOLY HAVE ALL OF THE SCOOP FOR
US TOMORROW.
>> I CANNOT WAIT TO SEE YOU ON
THAT RED CACARPET.
I KNOW YOU'RE GOING TO LOOK
SMASHING DARLING.
>> WE'LL SEE.
BUT WHEN YOU GO TO A FASHION
EVENT, I'M NOT LIKE YOU, IT'S
VERY SCARY.
I'M GOING TO REPORT.
SO I MAY NOT LOOK, YOU KNOW --
>> YOU'RE GOING TO LOOK
INCREDIBLE BECAUSE YOU'RE A
BEAUTIFUL GIRL AND YOU HAVE
GREAT STYLE, MY LOVE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> AND YOU'VE GOT A BEAUTIFUL
SMILE.
BUT I WILL TELL YOU, IT'S AN
INSIDER'S EVENT.
SO YOU'RE GOING TO SEE A LOT OF
PEOPLE THERE, YOU'RE GOING TO
SEE PEOPLE CLAMORING AROUND AND
YOU'LL BE LIKE WHO THE HECK IS
THAT?
IT REALLY IS A REAL FASHION
EVENT.
IT'S NOT NECESSARILY
STAR-STUDDED AS MUCH AS CFDA OR
THE OTHER ONE, MET.
>> AND IT'S THE OFFICIAL START
OF FASHION WEEK.
THERE ARE OTHER GALAS THROUGHOUT
THE YEAR BUT CELEBS GO AND
ATTEND.
THIS YEAR CELEBS EXPECTED TO BE
THERE LIKE JULIA ROBERTS, HEIDI
KLUM AND ANDY COHEN, BUT HE
PROBABLY WON'T BE THERE.
HE JUST WELCOMED HIS BABY.
HE'S OUT IN L.A.
>> HE WELCOMED LIZ BIG BABY
BENJAMIN, WHO'S 9 POUNDS.
I'M SO HAPPY FOR ANDY AND
EXCITED TO MEET HIM.
WE JUST TEXTED THIS MORNING.
AUNTY BEVY IS ON THE WAY.
>> NAOMI IS USUALLY THERE EVERY
YEAR ALSO.
NAOMI CAMPBELL, CURIOUS IF SHE
SHOWS UP TOO.
SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE IN TOWN.
>> I WILL LET YOU KNOW, CARLOS.
>> OF COURSE, DARLING.
>> I WONDER IF SHE HAS THE
NATURAL HAIR OR THE WEAVE.
>> I'LL LET YOU KNOW.
>> PLEASE DO.
>>> WE'LL HAVE ALL OF THE
EXCITEMENT ON TOMORROW'S SHOW.
BUT SPEAKING OF FASHION, WE HAVE
TO SAY "WAY TO GO" TO THE
LEGENDARY IRISH AFELL.
SHE'S 97 YEARS OLD AND MEGA
FASHIONISTA.
SO MUCH SO SHE JUST GOT SIGNED
TO THE MODELING AGENCY I AM G.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SHE'S BEEN AN ICON FOR YEARS.
THAT'S ME WITH HER AND MR.
MICKEY FROM PAPER MAGAZINE.
I MEAN, I HAVE BEEN TO SO MANY
EVENTS WITH HER OVER THE YEARS.
I JUST LOVE HER STYLE.
SHE'S A REAL INDEPENDENT, GUTSY
BROAD.
SHE SAID THAT'S THE REASON SHE
NEVER HAD A PROPER AGENT, SHE'S
A DO-IT-YOURSELF KIND OF GIRL.
NOW THAT SHE'S ALMOST 1200,
TOMMY HILFIGER PULLED HER TO THE
SIDE AND SAID BABE, I'M GOING TO
HELP YOU GET AN AGENT, HANDLE
YOUR BOOKING AND SCHEDULES.
I LOVE THAT.
IRIS RECENTLY LOST HER HUSBAND
IN 2015.
HE WAS 100 WHEN HE DIED.
HIS NAME WAS CARL.
THEY WERE INSPEP RABL.
THEY WERE QUITE THE DASHING
COUPLE.
I'M SO HAPPY IT SEE SHE HAS MORE
SUPPORT NOW THAT CARL IS NOT
THERE.
I SAY WAY TO GO AND IT GETS
GREATER LATER, IRIS!
>> SHE'S A NEW YORK STAPLE FOR
SURE.
BUT WE'RE ALSO SAYING "WAY TO GO
WEDNESDAY" TO EVERYONE INVOLVED
IN SHINE A LIGHT ON SLAVERY DAY
TOMORROW.
NEARLY 40 MILLION PEOPLE ARE
AFFECTED BY SLAVERY OF ALL KINDS
TO THIS DAY TODAY.
PEOPLE RAISED AWARENESS BY
MARKING A RED X ON THEIR HANDS.
SEVERAL CELEBRITIES ARE PART OF
THIS INITIATIVE, INCLUDING
CARRIE UNDERWOOD, ASHTON
KUTCHER, PEYTON MANNING, KRISTEN
BELL, COMMON, TONY HAWK, RUSSELL
WILSON AND LL COOL J.
THEY'VE ALL BEEN INVOLVED.
WAY TO GO.
>> AND PEOPLE THINK SLAVERY IS
SOMETHING GONE BUT MODERN DAY
SLAVERY IS QUITE THE PROBLEM
GLOBALLY.
>> LET US KNOW WHAT OTHER STARS
DESERVE A "WAY TO GO WEDNESDAY"
USING THE HASHTAG WGTW FOR YOUR
CHANCE TO GET A SHOUT OUT ON THE
SHOW.
>>> COMING UP, WE HAVE THE
INSIDE STORY ON THE BRITNEY
SPEARS ALBUM THAT WILL NEVER SEE
THE LIGHT OF DAY.DAY.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS THAT ONE.
THAT'S COMING UP.
-Morning.
-What do we got?
-Keep an eye on that branch.
Might get windy.
Have a good shift.
Fire pit.
Last use -- 0600.
I'd stay close.
Morning.
♪♪
Get ready to switch.
Protected by Flo.
Should say, "Protected
by Alan and Jamie."
-Right?
-Should it?
When you bundle
home and auto...
Run, Alan!
...you get more
than just savings.
You get 'round-the-clock
protection.
Now, eyeliner goes NYC-proof.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil
than just savings.
from Maybelline New York.
Smudge resistant.
Sweat resistant.
Waterproof.
Up to 36-hour wear.
New Tattoo Studio Gel Pencil.
Only from Maybelline New York.
♪ I'M A BIG KID NOW ♪
♪ WENT FROM BABY BOTTLES TO
DRINKING FROM SIPPY CUPS ♪
♪ WENT FROM WEARING DIAPERS TO
ROCKING THESE FRESH PULL-UPS ♪
♪ WE'RE 50 MILLION STRONG ♪
♪ SO PUT ON YOUR PULL-UPS
AND HELP US SING THIS SONG ♪
>>> "PAGE SIX TV NOW" -- BEN
AFFLECK AND LINDSAY SHOOKUS
SPLIT UP TO FOCUS ON THEIR
FAMILIES AND CAREERS, BUT A
SOURCE TELLS "PEOPLE" THEY
STRUCK UP A FRIENDSHIP AGAIN AND
I know it's hard Maddie.
But I promise,
it's gonna get better.
♪ ♪
(mom giggles)
(Thunderclap)
If your day doesn't
unfold as predicted.
Unfold this.
New Neutrogena®
Makeup Remover single.
And remove 99% of makeup.
100% rain or shine.
Neutrogena®.
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "PAGE SIX
TV."
NOW OFFSET'S DEBUT SOLO ALBUM
WAS SUPPOSED TO DROP ON HIS
BIRTHDAY, DECEMBER 14th.
BUT 54 DAYS LATER, WE'RE STILL
WAITING FOR THE NEW TUNES.
THE MIGOS RAPPER INSISTS THE
SOLO ALBUM WILL COME OUT ONCE
IT'S ACTUALLY READY.
YES, HE SAID ON INSTAGRAM THE
ALBUM WAS SMOKING HOT.
WHO SMOKE?
WE WANT SMOKE, SO STOP DELAYING
IT OR YOU WILL BE THE INFAMOUS
LIST OF LONG, LAST ALBUMS.
WHO IS HE IN DANGER OF JOINING?
>> THIS IS THE SIX LIST HERE.
AT NUMBER SIX IT'S THE CARTER V.
LIL WAYNE'S ALBUM WAS IN WELL
DOCUMENTED MUSIC PROGTORY FOR
NEARLY FIVE YEARS.
YOU HEARD THAT RIGHT.
BUT IT CAME OUT AND IS BETTER
THAN ANY OTHER ALBUM ON THIS
LIST.
I WILL TELL YOU THE ONES THAT
DID NOT COME OUT.
AT NUMBER FIVE, MADONNA.
BOTH PRODUCER JEFF PETTY BONE
SAID HE HAD NUMEROUS SCRAPPED
SONGS WITH HER THAT WILL NEVER
SEE THE LIGHT OF DAWES BECAUSE
SHE DECIDED TO GO ANOTHER
DIRECTION.
>> THAT DOESN'T MAKE IT AN
ALBUM, BUT OKAY.
>> SOUNDS LIKE THERE'S A LOT OF
SONGS THAT REQUEST MAKE AN
ALBUM.
KATY PERRY, SHE'S NUMBER FOUR ON
THE LIST BECAUSE SHE'S
RESUMEDERRED TO HAVE NOT ONE BUT
TWO CANCELED ALBUMS FROM BEFORE
HER SUPERSTARDOM.
>> DR. DRE IS NUMBER THREE ON
OUR LIST.
THERE WAS A 15-YEAR GAP BETWEEN
A SECOND AND THIRD ALBUM AND HE
HAS ANOTHER ALBUM "DETOX" THAT
WILL NEVER SEE THE LIGHT OF DAY
BECAUSE HE SAID IT'S DEAD.
>>> NUMBER TWO IS ADELE.
SHE'S STOPPED AN ENTIRE ALBUM OF
BEING A MOM BECAUSE SHE SAID IT
WAS GORPY.
>>> NUMBER ONE IS THE MOST
TRAGIC TO ME, BRITNEY SPEARS.
IN 2004 SHE TEASED SHE WAS
ALMOST DONE WITH HER NEXT ALBUM,
WHICH WAS CALLED "ORIGINAL
DOLL."
SHEEN PLAYED A TRACK FROM IT ON
THE RADIO CALLED "MONA LISA" BUT
IT NEVER CAME OUT.
THIS IS A CRAZY STORY.
BRITNEY SPEARS CALLED UP A RADIO
STATION, KISS-FM IN L.A., AND
BASICALLY SHOWED UP UNEXPECTED.
SHE PLAYED THE SONG.
>> WAS IT GOOD?
>> OF COURSE IT WAS GOOD.
NO, IT WAS.
I IT REALLY WAS.
I LISTENED TO IT THIS MORNING.
CAN YOU FIND IT ONLINE BUT IT
NEVER, EVER PLAYED AGAIN ON THE
RADIO.
THAT WAS THE ONE TIME IT PLAYED
AND HER HEP SAID, THE LABEL SAID
THIS ALBUM ISN'T COMING OUT.
>> WHICH IS WEIRD BECAUSE IN
2004, EVERY SINGLE SHE PUT OUT
WAS A HIT.
PEOPLE WERE REALLY ANTICIPATING
BRITNEY SPEARS SINGLES.
>> THEY STILL ARE, CARLOS.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN, SHE WAS
AT HER PEAK BACK THEN.
>> AND HER NEXT ALBUM WASN'T
UNTIL 2007.
"BLACKOUT," IT WAS A GREAT
ALBUM.
>> "BREAK THE ICE."
>> BRITNEY FANS COOL.
>> COME ON, REALLY?
BRITNEY FANS.
>>> COMING UP -- MICHAEL J.
JORDAN JUST MADEN JUST MADE AN W
DEAL.
WE'LL TELL WHAT YOU IT IS NEXT.
Hey guys!
Check out our new trick.
♪♪
Steady.. - Roger!
Steady.. Now!
Go all in for what you love
with Tony and Kellogg's
Frosted Flakes.
Now in delicious NEW
Honey Nut.
As part of this complete
breakfast.
They're gr-r-r-reat!
>>> CLOSED CAPTIONS ARE
SPONSORED BY --
by over
200 indoor
and outdoor
allergens.
Like those
from buddy.
Because stuffed
animals
are clearly no substitute
for real ones.
Feel the clarity.
And Live Claritin clear.
In one week...
a lot will happen in your life.
Wrinkles just
won't.
Neutrogena®
Rapid Wrinkle
Repair's
derm-proven retinol
works so fast,
it takes only one week
to reveal younger looking skin.
Neutrogena®
♪
Try new Nature Valley
Fruit & Nut Granola.
Never ending is now even better
at Olive Garden.
With all new
Never Ending Stuffed Pastas
starting at just $12.99.
Pick your favorite
stuffed pasta
like our new
Stuffed Ziti Fritta,
with your choice of
sauce and topping...
then try another
delicious combination.
Plus unlimited
salad and breadsticks.
It's all never ending.
Here's to more from
beginning to endless.
All New Never Ending Stuffed
Pastas starting at $12.99.
Only for a limited time,
at Olive Garden.
Brushing only reaches
25% of your mouth.
LISTERINE® cleans
virtually 100%.
Helping to prevent gum
disease and bad breath.
Never settle for 25%.
Always go for 100.
Bring Out the Bold™
>>> WELCOME BACK TO "PAGE SIX
TV."
IT'S FEBRUARY, WHICH ALSO MEANS
IT'S BLACK HISTORY MONTH.
[ APPLAUSE ]
CLAP IT UP, GUYS!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WE'RE ALSO SHOUTING OUT BLACK
EXCELLENCE MONTH, MICHAEL B.
JORDAN, THAT'S RIGHT.
HIS PRODUCTION COMPANY OUTLIERS
SOCIETY INKED A TV DEAL WITH
AMAZON WHICH WHICH INCLUDE
INCLUSION WRITERS AND STIPULATE
INCLUSIVE WRITINGS FOR ALL CAST
AND CREW.
THIS IS A BIG DEAL, ISN'T IT?
>> THIS IS A BIG DEAL.
IT'S HISTORIC IN THAT IT'S THE
FIRST OF THE KIND THAT THE
NETWORK ADOPTED THE INCLUSION
RIDER.
WAY TO GO, MICHAEL B. JORDAN.
>> WALKING THE WALKING AND
TALKING THE TALK AND DOING IT
LOOKING VERY GOOD.
>>> FOR THE BREAKING STORIES, GO
TO PAGESIX.COM.
AND REMEMBER, IF YOU DON'T WANT
IT ON "PAGE SIX" --
>> DON'T DO IT!
(Thunderclap)
If your day doesn't
unfold as predicted.
Unfold this.
New Neutrogena®
Makeup Remover single.
And remove 99% of makeup.
100% rain or shine.
Neutrogena®.
There's the same old
way to get smooth,
And then there's New
Fructis Sleek Shot.
Our first
in-shower styler.
Infused with plant protein.
Just mix a shot with shampoo.
And power up with lather.
5x smoother hair.
Half the time.
It does the work for you,
So you can skip the flat iron.
Out with the old,
And in with
the smooth.
New Fructis Sleek Shot
In-Shower Styler.
By Garnier, naturally.
In one week...
a lot will happen in your life.
Wrinkles just
won't.
Neutrogena®
Rapid Wrinkle
Repair's
derm-proven retinol
works so fast,
it takes only one week
to reveal younger looking skin.
Making wrinkles look
so last week.
Rapid Wrinkle Repair®
Pair with new retinol oil
for 2X the wrinkle
fighting power.
Neutrogena®