Captioning sponsored by
NEWSHOUR PRODUCTIONS, LLC
>> Woodruff: GOOD EVENING, I'M
JUDY WOODRUFF.
ON THE NEWSHOUR TONIGHT, A HOUSE
DIVIDED-- PRESIDENT TRUMP
DELIVERS HIS STATE OF THE UNION
AFTER THE LONGEST GOVERNMENT
SHUTDOWN AND NO DEAL IN SIGHT
FOR A BORDER WALL.
WE TALK WITH LAWMAKERS,
HISTORIAN MICHAEL BESCHLOSS PUTS
THE ADDRESS IN CONTEXT, AND OUR
PANEL PREVIEWS WHAT IS AT STAKE
FOR THE PRESIDENT.
PLUS, MR. TRUMP'S PLAN TO KEEP
FORCES IN IRAQ TO MONITOR IRAN
SPARKS CONDEMNATION IN BAGHDAD
AND CALLS FOR THE U.S. TO LEAVE.
ALL THAT AND MORE ON TONIGHT'S
PBS NEWSHOUR.
>> MAJOR FUNDING FOR THE PBS
NEWSHOUR HAS BEEN PROVIDED BY:
AMERICAN CRUISE LINES FLEET OF
SMALL SHIPS EXPLORE AMERICAN
LANDMARKS, LOCAL CULTURES AND
CALM WATERWAYS.
AMERICAN CRUISE LINES, PROUD
SPONSOR OF PBS NEWSHOUR.
>> ORDERING TAKEOUT.
>> FINDING THE WEST ROUTE.
>> TALKING FOR HOURS.
>> PLANNING FOR SHOWERS.
>> YOU CAN DO THE THINGS YOU
LIKE TO DO WITH A WIRELESS PLAN
DESIGNED FOR YOU.
ARN MORE ATULAR.D DATA.
consumercellular.tv
>> BABBEL.
A LANGUAGE APP THAT TEACHES
REAL-LIFE CONVERSATIONS IN A NEW
LANGUAGE.
>> AND WITH THE ONGOING SUPPORT
OF THESE INSTITUTIONS:
>> THIS PROGRAM WAS MADE
POSSIBLE BY THE CORPORATION FOR
PUBLIC BROADCASTING.
AND BY CONTRIBUTIONS TO YOUR PBS
STATION FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> Woodruff: THIS IS STATE OF
THE UNION NIGHT, AND THE BATTLE
LINES ARE DRAWN.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS PRESIDENT
TRUMP WILL APPEAL FOR UNITY,
EVEN AS HE HOLDS TO HIS DEMAND
FOR A BORDER WALL.
NEWLY RESURGENT DEMOCRATS SAY
THE PRESIDENT HIMSELF IS THE
PROBLEM.
THE SPLIT WAS CLEAR AT THE
CAPITOL TODAY AS MR. TRUMP'S
SUPPORTERS AND OPPONENTS SOUNDED
OFF.
>> I THINK HE'S GOING TO DO A
GOOD JOB AND I THINK HE REALLY
IS MAKING AN EFFORT.
HE'LL MAKE SOME STATEMENTS
TONIGHT THAT'LL SURPRISE A LOT
OF PEOPLE ON THE OTHER SIDE.
AND I'M TALKING ABOUT
CONCILIATORY THINGS.
AND I THINK IT COMES FROM THE
HEART.
THIS GUY IS-- HE HAS BACKGROUND
THAT HAS SHOWN HIM IN DIFFERENT
LIGHTS AND HE'S ALWAYS BEEN
SUCCESSFUL.
>> WELL THE PRESIDENT HASN'T
BEEN ACTING ON UNITY FOR TWO
YEARS UP AND DOWN THE LINE.
HE'S ALWAYS CRITICIZING,
DIVIDING, AND SO IF HE CALLS FOR
UNITY TONIGHT WE'LL HAVE TO SAY
WHAT HAPPENS TOMORROW AND THE
DAY AFTER AND THE DAY AFTER.
BECAUSE IN PAST HE'S CALLED FOR
UNITY AND HAS FORGOTTEN ABOUT IT
BY THE NEXT MORNING.
>> Woodruff: THE FORMAL
DEMOCRATIC RESPONSE TONIGHT WILL
COME FROM STACEY ABRAMS.
SHE NARROWLY LOST HER BID LAST
YEAR TO BECOME GEORGIA'S FIRST
BLACK GOVERNOR AND IS NOW A
RISING STAR IN THE PARTY.
LET'S TURN NOW TO OUR LISA
DESJARDINS AT THE CAPITOL AND
YAMICHE ALCINDOR AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
YAMICHE, TO YOU FIRST.
I HAVE BEEN TALKING TO FOLKS AT
THE WHITE HOUSE, MUCH OF IT OFF
THE RECORD.
YOU'VE BEEN TALKING TO THEM,
TOO.
WHAT DO WE KNOW FOR CERTAIN, OR
WHAT DO WE THINK THE PRESIDENT
WILL FOCUS ON TONIGHT?
>> THE PRESIDENT WILL FOCUS ON
UNIFYING OUR NATION AND UNIFYING
BOTH POLITICAL PARTIES, BUT
SOME, OF COURSE, SAY THERE ARE
SOME CREDIBILITY ISSUES THERE
BECAUSE OF HIS POLITICAL TRACK
RECORD OF REALLY OFFENDING AND
GIVING INSULTS TO HIS POLITICAL
OPPONENTS.
THE PRESIDENT IS EXPECTED TO
TALK ABOUT A NUMBER OF TOPICS,
INCLUDING ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION,
HEALTHCARE COSTS, INCLUDING
TRADE, AND WARS AND FOREIGN
POLICY AS WELL AS
INFRASTRUCTURE.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE AT SOME
POINT PITCHING AND ASKING
CONGRESS TO COME UP WITH SOME
SORT OFEN FRACTURE PLAN.
THE PRESIDENT'S ALSO SUPPOSED TO
BE TALKING ABOUT H.I.V./AIDS AND
TRYING TO END THE@
OF THAT DEADLY DISEASE BY 2030.
THE PRESIDENT IS ALSO SUPPOSED
TO BE TALKING ABOUT HIS IDEAS
FOR A WAY FORWARD.
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT, THOUGH,
TO REMIND PEOPLE THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAS BEEN TWEETING
TODAY AND HE'S BEEN SAYING THAT
CHUCK SCHUMER'S MAD THAT HE
DIDN'T WIN THE SENATE.
HE'S SAID IN THE PAST THAT
DEMOCRATS DON'T BELIEVE IN
BORDER SECURITY, SO WHILE THE
PRESIDENT PUTS FORWARD THIS
UNIFYING MESSAGE, PEOPLE ARE
SAYING, JUST LOOK AT WHAT YOU
TWEETED TODAY THAT WILL BE
HURTING THAT UNIFYING MESSAGE.
>> Woodruff: LISA, WE KNOW THE
OTHER PARTY ALWAYS PREPARES FOR
WHAT THE PRESIDENT IS GOING TO
SAY.
WHAT ARE DEMOCRATS SAYING ABOUT
HOW THEY PLAN TO HANDLE, WHAT
THEY EXPECT THE PRESIDENT TO SAY
AND HOW THEY WILL RESPOND TO IT?
>> DEMOCRATS ARE MORE EXCITED
ABOUT THIS RESPONSE THAN I'VE
HEARD THEM IN SOME TIME.
STACY ABRAMS TO THEM REPRESENTS
A SHIFT AWAY FROM PLAYING IT
SAFE.
THERE IS ONE LONG-TIME
PROGRESSIVE WHO TOLD ME TONIGHT,
WE'VE BEEN PLAYING IT TOO SAFE
AS DEMOCRATS.
WE WANT SOMEONE WHO HAS A CLEAR,
AGGRESSIVE AGENDA LIKE STACY
ABRAMS, WHO TALKS ABOUT VOTER
RIGHTS.
SHE ALSO REPRESENTS SOME OTHER
IMPORTANT THEMES FOR DEMOCRATS
TONIGHT, DIVERSITY IN TWO WAYS.
ONE, SHE WILL BE FIRST AFRICAN
AMERICAN WOMAN TO GIVE A MAJOR
PARTY RESPONSE.
ALSO, THOUGH, SHE WILL BE THE
FIRST NON-ELECTED OFFICIAL.
SHE NO LONGER HOLDS OFFICE,
HAVING LOST THE GUBERNATORIAL
RACE LAST FALL, SHE WILL BE THE
FIRST NON-ELECTED OFFICIAL TO
GIVE THIS KIND OF RESPONSE SOME
A SORT OF OUTSIDER AND ALSO A
CORE PART OF THE DEMOCRATIC
BASE.
THIS ALSO STICKS TO A THEME
WE'LL SEE VISUALLY ON THE FLOOR,
DEMOCRATIC WOMEN IN THE HOUSE
WILL BE WEARING ALL WHITE.
THEY SAY THAT IS TO SHOW A SIGN,
A REFERENCE TO THE SUFFER GETS,
BUT ONE OF THEM TOLD ME IT'S
SMART VISUAL CUE.
THEY WANT THE HIGHLIGHT THE
GIVES BETWEEN DEMOCRATS AND
THEIR INCREASED DIVERSITY THIS
THIS CONGRESS AND REPUBLICANS,
WHO HAVE LESS I DIVERSITY IN THS
CONGRESS.
>> Woodruff: LISA, STAYING
WITH YOU, YAMICHE MENTIONED THE
PRESIDENT IS SUPPOSED TO TALK
TONIGHT ABOUT BORDER SECURITY.
WHAT DO WE KNOW AT THIS POINT
ABOUT WHERE THE CONFERENCE
COMMITTEE WORKING ON THAT ISSUE
FOR THE LAST SEVERAL DAYS, THEY
HAVE A DEADLINE FACING THEM.
I TALKED TODAY TO SPEAKER PELOSI
AND MINORITY LEADER CHUCK
SCHUMER.
THEY SAID PROGRESS IS BEING
MADE.
WHAT ARE YOU HEARING?
>> MY REPORTING IS THE SAME.
TALKING TO OTHER LEADERS AND
PEOPLE WHO ARE ON THE CONFERENCE
MEE.
THERE IS REAL PROGRESS ON THE
STAFF LEVEL.
THEY THINK THEY COULD COME UP
WITH A DEAL IF IT IS JUST LEFT
TO THE MEMBERS OF THE
APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE ALONE.
JUDY, THE CONFERENCE COMMITTEE
WILL HAVE AN UNUSUAL MEETING
TOMORROW MORNING, CLOSED DOOR,
WITH CAREER BORDER PATROL
OFFICIALS.
NOW, IT'S NOT CLEAR WHY THAT'S
CLOSED DOOR, BUT ONE STAFFER
TOLD ME THAT THEY THINK IT'S
BECAUSE THEY WANT THE QUESTIONS
AND ANSWERS TO BE AS FORTHRIGHT
AS POSSIBLE.
THEY ARE LOOKING AT TRYING TO
GET A CONFERENCE REPORT BY THE
END OF THE WEEK OR THIS WEEKEND
AT THE LATEST.
THEY THINK IT'S DOABLE, BUT
THERE ARE MANY X FACTORS, ONE OF
THE BIGGEST BEING THE PRESIDENT
AND WHAT HE SAYS TONIGHT ABOUT
BORDER SECURITY.
>> Woodruff: AND FINALLY,
YAMICHE, WHAT DO WE KNOW ABOUT
HOW THE PRESIDENT IS PLANNING
FOR TONIGHT AND ALSO
TRADITIONALLY THE PRESIDENT HAS
GUESTS COME TO THE CAPITAL.
WHO DO WE KNOW THOSE TO BE?
>> THE PRESIDENT IS USING
NATIONAL STAGE TO MAKE THE CASE
THAT THE STATE OF THE UNION IS
GREAT BUT THAT IT WOULD BE
BETTER IF THERE WERE CONCERNS
MET AND PEOPLE PAID ATTENTION TO
THE CONCERNS THAT HE HAS.
RIGHT BEHIND ME AT THE WHITE
HOUSE, THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN
PREPARING AND REALLY USING THIS
SPEECH AS A WAY TO PREPARE
HIMSELF TO TALK ON A
TELEPROMPTER.
HE HAD A TELEPROMPTER ACTUALLY
BROUGHT INTO THE WHITE HOUSE, SO
HE'S GOING TO TRY THE MAKE SURE
HE'S READING PROPERLY.
THE OTHER THING HE'S GOING TO BE
DOING IS BRINGING IN GUESTS.
THE GUESTS HE'S BRINGING IN ARE
ONE, FAMILY WHOSE FAMILY MEMBER
WAS MURDERED OR KILLED BY AN
UNDOCUMENTED IMMIGRANT.
THE PRESIDENT'S ULTIMATELY
BRINGING A LITTLE BOY NAMED
JOSHUA TRUMP WHO WAS BULLIED
BECAUSE OF HIS LAST NAME, WHICH
HE PLAYS WITH THE PRESIDENT, AND
THE PRESIDENT IS ALSO BRINGING
SOMEONE WHO WAS FREED BY THE
CRIMINAL JUSTICE REFORM ACT THAT
WAS PASSED BY BOTH PARTIES.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS WE WANTS
BIPARTISANSHIP.
THIS PERSON WHO CAME OUT OF
PRISON IS EMBODYING WHAT WE
COULD BE DOING IN THE FUTURE.
>> YAMICHE ALCINDOR AT THE WHITE
HOUSE, LISA DESJARDINS AT THE
CAPITOL.
WE WILL CERTAINLY COME BACK TO
THE TWO OF YOU LATER TONIGHT
WHEN WE HAVE OUR SPECIAL
COVERAGE.
THANKS.
WE WANT THE HEAR FROM LAWMAKERS
NOW.
REPRESENTATIVE JAMES CLYBURN OF
SOUTH CAROLINA IS THE THIRD
HIGHEST RANKING DEMOCRAT IN THE
U.S. HOUSE.
HE JOINS US FROM CAPITOL HILL.
REPRESENTATIVE CLYBURN, THANK
YOU VERY MUCH FOR JOINING US.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Woodruff: WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING FOR TRUMP TO SAY
TONIGHT?
>> WELL, THE PRESIDENT IS ASKING
US TO CHOOSE GREATNESS, AND I
WOULD HOPE THAT WE HEAR SOME
GREATNESS FROM HIM.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I HAVE BEEN
READING A LOT OF "DEMOCRACY IN
AMERICA" OF LATE.
IT TELLS US THAT AMERICA'S
GREATNESS IS NOT BECAUSE WE ARE
MORE ENLIGHTENED THAN ANY OTHER
COUNTRY, BUT BECAUSE WE HAVE
ALWAYS BEEN ABLE TO REPAIR OUR
FAULTS.
I WOULD HOPE THAT THE PRESIDENT
TONIGHT WILL DEMONSTRATE THAT
KIND OF GREATNESS.
SUPPOSE SOME THINGS THAT WE CAN
DO TO REPAIR OUR FAULTS.
THEY HAVE BEEN HIGHLIGHTED QUITE
A BIT IN THE LAST SEVERAL
MONTHS, AND I AM HOPEFUL THAT
WHATEVER HE SAYS TONIGHT WILL
BRING US TOGETHER AS A PEOPLE,
MOVE US FORWARD AS A COUNTRY,
AND MAKE US REALLY GREAT.
>> Woodruff: WHERE DO YOU SEE
THERE COULD BE COMMON GROUND?
WHO WHITE -- THE WHITE HOUSE SAS
WE'VE TRIED THE MAKE OVERTURES
TO DEMOCRATS ON BORDER SECURITY.
THEY HAVEN'T MET EYE TO EYE WITH
US.
THEY TICK OFF A NUMBER OVER
ISSUES WHERE THEY SAY DEMOCRATS
HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO MEET THEM
HALFWAY.
WHAT DO YOU -- WHERE DO YOU SEE
POTENTIAL COMMON GROUND?
>> WELL, I THINK THAT THERE'S
COMMON GROUND TO BE HAD ON
BORDER SECURITY.
THE PRESIDENT SEEMS TO HAVE
BACKED AWAY FROM HIS CONCRETE,
30-FOOT-HIGH WALL AND IS NOW
TALKING ABOUT MORE BROADER
SECURITY.
HE'S TALKING ABOUT BARRIERS.
AND WE TOO HAVE BACKED AWAY FROM
OUR POSITIONS OF NO MONEY FOR
ANY KIND OF WALL.
WE ARE ADVOCATING A SMART WALL,
USING 21st CENTURY TECHNOLOGY
TO MAKE THIS WALL AS SMART AS WE
HAVE MADE OUR TELEPHONES AND OUR
TELEVISIONS.
SO WE CAN HAVE A SMART WALL, ONE
THAT WILL USE DRONES TO KEEP
ANYBODY FROM FLYING OVER IT, USE
X-RAY EQUIP TO KEEP ANYBODY FROM
GETTING AROUND IT, USE SCANNERS
TO KEEP ANYBODY FROM BURROWING
UNDER IT UNDETECTED.
SO WE CAN DO THIS IN A SMART
WAY.
I JUST CAME BACK FROM
BROWNSVILLE, TEXAS.
WE WERE AT A PORT OFEN TRY.
-- PORT OF ENTRY.
I SAW A PORT IN DIRE NEED OF
RETROFITTING.
I SAW FENCING THAT'S ALREADY
THERE IN DIRE NEED OF REPAIRING.
I DO BELIEVE THAT WE CAN DO WHAT
IS NECESSARY TO SECURE OUR
BORDER, JUST DO IT IN A SMART
WAY, NOT TO BUILD A MONUMENT TO
ANYBODY.
>> Woodruff: SO TO BE CLEAR,
YOU'RE SAYING DEMOCRATS, YOU'RE
THIRD IN LINE IN LEADERSHIP IN
THE HOUSE, THE DEMOCRATS ARE
PREPARED TO SUPPORT THE MONEY
FOR SOME SORT OF PHYSICAL
BARRIER?
>> SO LONG AS IT'S DONE SMARTLY.
I BELIEVE THAT WE WILL VOTE FOR
WHATEVER THAT COMMITTEE COMES
OUT.
IF THEY COME OUT WITH A
BIPARTISAN AROACH -- APPROACH TO
GET THIS DONE, IRRESPECTIVE OF
HOW THEY PUT IT TOGETHER, I DO
BELIEVE YOU'LL GET EXTENSIVE
SUPPORT AMONG DEMOCRATS FOR IT.
IT MAY NOT BE UNANIMOUS, BUT
THERE WILL BE A LOT OF UNITY.
>> Woodruff: ARE DEMOCRATS
PREPARED TO SHOW RESPECT TO THE
PRESIDENT TONIGHT?
I ASKED THAT, BECAUSE WE
REMEMBER UNDER PRESIDENT OBAMA
THERE WERE STATE OF THE UNION
ADDRESSES WHEN MEMBERS CALLED
OUT TO HIM, ONE OF THEM CALLING
HIM A LIAR.
HOW DO YOU SEE TONIGHT GOING?
>> I THINK YOU'LL SEE US BEING
VERY RESPECTFUL.
YOU KNOW, MY DAD USED TO TEACH
US ALL THE TIME THAT THE FIRST
LINE -- SIGN OF A GOOD EDUCATION
IS GOOD MANNERS.
SO I TRY TO PUT MY EDUCATION ON
DISPLAY EVERY TIME I WALK ENTER
THE HALLS OF CONGRESS OR THE
HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES.
YOU MAY REMEMBER WHEN THAT YELL
WAS MADE, I'M THE ONE THAT LED
THE CHARGE TO GET A RESOLUTION
OF DISAPPROVAL FOR WHAT MY
COLLEAGUE SAID THAT NIGHT, AND
IT PASSED THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES, AND I THINK
THAT WE SHOWED THEN THAT WE
DISAPPROVE OF SUCH ACTIONS, AND
WE CERTAINLY ARE NOT GOING TO DO
ANYTHING TO VIOLATE WHAT WE DID
LAST YEAR.
>> Woodruff: CONGRESSMAN
CLYBURN, WHAT OTHER AREAS DO YOU
SEE DEMOCRATS AND REPUBLICANS
AND THE WHITE HOUSE WORKING
TOGETHER ON THIS YEAR?
>> OH, I THINK WE CAN DO A
COMPREHENSIVEN -- COMPREHENSIVE
INFRASTRUCTURE DEAL.
I THINK IT'S NECESSARY FOR US TO
DEVELOP OUR RURAL COMMUNITIES.
WE NEED TO BE PUTTING IN WATER
AND SEWERS.
WE NEED TO BE REPAIRING ROADS
AND BRIDGES.
WE NEED TO BE BUILDING SCHOOLS
IN OUR RURAL AREAS.
WE CAN DO A COMPREHENSIVE BILL
THAT WOULD HAVE BROAD BAPPED
DEPLOYMENT GOING INTO THESE
RURAL COMMUNITIES.
TOO MANY OF THEM ARE BEING LEFT
BEHIND.
WE NEED TO MAKE THIS INVESTMENT.
IT WILL PAY OFF HANDSOMELY IF WE
DO, AND I REALLY BELIEVE IT CAN
BE DONE IN A BIPARTISAN WAY.
>> Woodruff: CONGRESSMAN JAMES
CLYBURN, THE WHIP FOR THE
DEMOCRATS IN THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Woodruff: AS WE HEARD,
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS EXPECTED TO
DOUBLE DOWN IN HIS SPEECH
TONIGHT, CALLING ON CONGRESS TO
FUND A WALL ALONG THE SOUTHERN
BORDER.
ONE OPTION HE HASN'T RULED OUT--
DECLARING A NATIONAL EMERGENCY
TO BUILD THE WALL, IS CAUSING A
SPLIT AMONG SENATE REPUBLICANS.
SENATOR LINDSEY GRAHAM WARNED
YESTERDAY THERE COULD BE A WAR
WITHIN THE G.O.P. OVER THE WALL.
WE TURN NOW TO ONE OF THE
PRESIDENT'S STRONGEST ALLIES IN
CONGAS SENATOR DAVID PERDUE OF
GEORGIA.
SENATOR, THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR
JOINING US.
I THINK YOU WERE THERE.
WELL, THERE YOU ARE.
SENATOR, HOW MUCH OF A DIVIDE IS
THERE STILL DO YOU THINK BETWEEN
REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS,
BETWEEN DEMOCRATS AND THE WHITE
HOUSE OVER WHAT IS GOING TO
HAPPEN WITH REGARD TO A BARRIER,
A WALL AT THE SOUTHERN BORDER?
>> WELL, I HOPE THAT IT'S
NARROWING, JUDY.
THIS IS A SITUATION WHERE WE'RE
DEALING WITH A TOPIC THAT BOAST
SIDES ARE MAKING THE SAME
ARGUMENT I MEAN, THIS IS THE
FIFTH PRESIDENT IN A ROW THAT'S
ASKED CONGRESS FOR BORDER
FUNDING TO BUILD A WALL.
I MEAN, H.W. BUSH BUILT THE
FIRST MILE.
EVEN BARACK OBAMA BUILT 135
MILES OF WALL.
BOTH PARTIES AGREE THAT THIS IS
A NATIONAL SECURITY ISSUE, AND
WE NEED TO DO IT NOW.
THE PROBLEM IS THE HYPOCRISY OF
POLITICS HAVE BROUGHT US TO THIS
POINT.
I'M HOPEFUL THAT THIS CONFERENC
COMMITTEE IS GOING TO GET TO A
BIPARTISAN SOLUTION HERE THAT WE
I'M HOPEFUL THAT WILL, JUDY.
>> Woodruff: AS YOU KNOW,
SENATOR, DURING THE CAMPAIGN
OVER TWO YEARS AGO, THE
PRESIDENT WAS TALKING ABOUT A
WALL.
AT TIMES HE SPOKE ABOUT A
CONCRETE WALL.
AT TIMES HE SPOKE ABOUT SEA TO
SHINING SEA.
THE PRESIDENT HAS CHANGED WHAT
HE'S ASKING FOR, ISN'T THAT FAIR
TO SAY?
>> THIS IS MAN WHO IS, NUMBER
ONE, TRYING TO PROTECT THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
HE'S FIGHTING FOR OUR NATIONAL
SECURITY.
THERE ARE 2,000 MILES OF THAT
SOUTHERN BORDER.
650 MILES, JUDY, ALREADY HAVE
SOME SORT OF BARRIER ON IT.
AND HE'S ASKING FOR A LITTLE
MORE THAN 200 MILES.
SO I THINK THAT PUTS IT IN
PERSPECTIVE, BUT HI WANTS IT TO
BE PUT IN POSITIONS WHERE DRUG
TRAFFICKING, HUMAN TRAFFICKING,
AND ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION IS
HAPPENING IN THE MOST SEVERE
MANNER RIGHT NOW.
>> Woodruff: FROM WHAT YOU
KNOW, WE JUST HEARD CONGRESSMAN
CLYBURN SAY HE BELIEVES THERE
CAN BE SUCCESS IN THAT
CONFERENCE COMMITTEE.
LEFT TO THEIR OWN DEVICES, THEY
CAN COME UP WITH AN AGREEMENT.
ARE YOU OPTIMISTIC THAT'S GOING
THE HAPPEN, AS WELL?
>> I'M HOPEFUL.
I'M NOT SURE I'M OPTIMISTIC YET.
WE'LL KNOW TOMORROW, BECAUSE
THESE ARE NON-POLITICAL PEOPLE
WHO ARE COMING UP TO GIVE SOME
ADVICE TO THE COMMITTEE.
I'M HOPEFUL TOMORROW WE'LL HEAR
SOME STATEMENTS COMING OUT OF
THAT CONFERENCE COMMITTEE THAT
WILL GIVE US OPTIMISM ABOUT
GETTING PAST THIS IMPASSE.
THE OTHER THING, JUDY, THIS IS
RIDICULOUS.
THIS IS AN APPROPRIATION ISSUE
THAT SHOULD HAVE BEEN DEALT WITH
BEFORE SEPTEMBER 30th LAST
YEAR.
WE'RE IN THE FIFTH MONTH OF OUR
NEW FISCAL YEAR.
SO I'M HOPEFUL THAT EVERYBODY
WILL GET THIS DONE THIS WEEK.
>> Woodruff: I THINK YOU KNOW,
SENATOR, THE PRESIDENT IS STILL
NOT RULING OUT THE IDEA OF
DECLARING A NATIONAL EMERGENCY
IN ORDER TO GO AHEAD AND BUILD
THE WALL, PUT MONEY ASIDE TO
BUILD THE WALL IF THERE IS NO
AGREEMENT IN CONGRESS.
BUT HE HAS BEEN TOLD BY SENATE
MAJORITY LEADER, YOUR COLLEAGUE
SENATOR McCONNELL, MITCH
McCONNELL, THAT THAT'S NOT A
GOOD IDEA.
DO YOU THINK THE PRESIDENT STILL
WOULD SERIOUSLY CONSIDER DOING
THAT?
>> WELL, HE HAS SAID HE WOULD,
AND I TAKE HIM AT HIS WORD, BUT
AGAIN, THIS IS MAN, I THINK
TONIGHT IN THE STATE OF THE
UNION, YOU'LL HEAR PRESIDENT
TRUMP OFFER A LITTLE MORE
CONCILIATORY TONE, BECAUSE HE'S
A DEALMAKER FIRST AND LAST, WE
ALL KNOW THAT.
HE JUST WANTS TO GET BORDER
SECURITY MOVING IN THE RIGHT
DIRECTION AND BOTH PARTIES
ACTUALLY WANT THAT.
SO I'M HOPEFUL THAT TONIGHT
WE'LL SEE A LITTLE MORE OF THAT.
AND THEN OVER THE NEXT WEEK OR
SO, WE'LL SEE SOMETHING COME OUT
OF THIS CONFERENCE COMMITTEE
THAT WILL PRECLUDE THE NEED FOR
THE PRESIDENT TO DO SOMETHING
EXTREME.
HE CERTAINLY HAS THE RIGHT TO DO
IT, BUT I'M HOPEFUL CONGRESS
WILL STEP IN HERE AND DO ITS
JOB.
>> Woodruff: SENATOR, HOW DOES
IT CHANGE WHAT THE PRESIDENT CAN
DO BECAUSE DEMOCRATS HAVE NOW
WON THE MAJORITY IN THE HOUSE OF
REPRESENTATIVES?
HE IS DEALING WITH A DIFFERENT
CONGRESS THAN HE WAS LAST YEAR.
>> WELL, WE HAVE AN HISTORIC
OPPORTUNITY.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT TIP O'NEILL
AND REAGAN, YOU THINK ABOUT NEWT
GINGRICH AND BILL CLINTON, WHEN
YOU HAD SPLIT GOVERNMENT IS WHEN
REALLY BIG THINGS DID HAPPEN
HERE, SO THE ANSWER IS NANCY
PELOSI HAS A CHOICE AS THE
SPEAKER.
EITHER SHE IS GOING TO WORK WITH
THIS PRESIDENT WHO HAS BEEN
PROVEN HE WILL MAKE A DEAL, AND
HE DID AN HISTORIC BIPARTISAN
BILL JUST THIS PAST YEAR, JUDY,
THAT REALLY HELPED SMALL BANKS.
I'M LOOKING FOR MORE OF THAT.
SO I THINK THE SPEAKER HAS TO
MAKE A DECISION.
IS SHE GOING TO LEGISLATE WITH
THIS PRESIDENT, WHO IS MORE THAN
WILLING TO DO, THAT OR IS SHE
GOING TO INVESTIGATE GOING INTO
THE PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION GOING
INTO 2020.
>> Woodruff: MY QUESTION IS:
HOW DOES IT CHANGE WHAT THE
PRESIDENT IS ABLE TO DO?
>> IF THEY DON'T OPERATE WITH
US, IT MOVES BACK IN THE SENATE,
ALL WE'LL BE FOCUSED ON IS THE
CONFIRMATION, AND LEADER
McCONNELL HAS TALKED ABOUT
BEING MORE AGGRESSIVE ABOUT
GETTING THE CONFIRMATION DONE
THIS YEAR AND NEXT.
SO WE KNOW WE CAN DO THAT.
THAT'S IN THE HANDS OF THE
SENATE.
I JUST IMPLORE THE SENATE OR THE
HOUSE MEMBERS TO PUT PRESSURE ON
LEADERSHIP THERE.
LET'S GET TOGETHER AND
LEGISLATE, WHICH IS WHY THE
PEOPLE IN AMERICA SENT US UP
HERE.
>> Woodruff: THERE IS A REPORT
OUT IN THE LAST FEW DAYS,
SENATOR, ABOUT THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION STILL NOT HAVING
SUBMITTED NAMES FOR HUNDREDS OF
EMPTY POSITIONS INSIDE THE
ADMINISTRATION.
DO YOU HAVE AN EXPLANATION FOR
WHY THAT IS?
>> YEAH, WE'VE HAD AN HISTORIC
LEVEL OF OBSTRUCTION FIRST OF
ALL.
>> Woodruff: NO, I'M --
>> NO, I UNDERSTAND.
THE GOOD NEWS IS WE HAVE
CONFIRMED OVER 85 JUDGES, 30
COURTS OF APPEAL JUDGE, AND TWO
SUPREME COURT JUSTICES.
BUT THIS IS AN HISTORIC
SITUATION, JUDY, WHERE THIS IS
THE FIRST TIME IN U.S. HISTORY
THE MINORITY PARTY HAS IN THE
WAIVED THE 30-HOUR RULE IN THE
SENATE.
HAVING SAID THAT, THERE ARE OVER
300 NOMINATIONS AT THE END OF
LAST YEAR WAITING TO BE
CONFIRMED.
WE NEED TO GET DOWN TO BUSINESS
AND GET PAST THIS AND STOP
PLAYING PARTISAN POLITICS.
THIS PRESIDENT, IF WE DON'T
CHANGE THE RULE AND WE DON'T
MOVE PAST THIS, THIS PRESIDENT
WON'T EVEN BE ABLE TO PUT HIS
FULL COMPLEMENT OF GOVERNMENT
TOGETHER.
>> Woodruff: I'M ASKING ABOUT
THOSE POSITIONS FOR WHICH NAMES
HAVE NOT EVEN BEEN PUT FORWARD
YET?
>> FIRST OF ALL, THERE ARE
PLENTY OF NAMES THAT HAVE BEEN
BEEN PUT FORWARD THAT HAVE NOT
BEEN BROUGHT FORWARD BECAUSE OF
THE OBSTRUCTION OF THE DEMOCRATS
IN THE SENATE.
WHEN THAT HAPPEN, I CAN PROMISE
YOU, THIS PRESIDENT WILL LINE
THEM UP IN TERMS OF NOMINEES
WAITING TO BE CONFIRMED.
>> Woodruff: SENATOR DAVID
PERDUE OF GEORGIA, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
>> THANKS, JUDY.
>> Woodruff: SO LET'S TAKE A
STEP BACK NOW AND PUT THIS
MOMENT IN TONIGHT'S ADDRESS IN
CONTEXT WITH PRESIDENTIAL
HISTORIAN AND NEWSHOUR REGULAR
MICHAEL BESCHLOSS.
MICHAEL BESCHLOSS, WONDERFUL TO
SEE YOU.
>> WONDERFUL TO SEE YOU ALWAYS.
>> Woodruff: THANK YOU FOR
BEING HERE.
>> THANK YOU, JUDY.
>> Woodruff: SO YOU'VE LOOKED
AT HOW PRESIDENTS HAVE HANDLED
TIMES OF STRESS, TIMES WHEN THEY
ARE FACING OPPOSITION, WHETHER
NEW OR LONGSTANDING.
THAT SEEMS TO BE CERTAINLY WHAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS FACING
TONIGHT.
HOW HAVE OTHER PRESIDENTS
HANDLED IT?
>> WELL, OFTENTIMES THEY'VE MADE
A PIVOT.
BILL CLINTON, FOR INSTANCE, IN
1996 WAS ACTED TO RUN FOR
REELECTION, AND TWO YEARS
EARLIER HE HAD LOST CONGRESS TO
THE REPUBLICANS FIRST■ TIME IN 0
YEARS.
THAT WAS A VERY BIG EVENT.
SO HE SAID, WE REMEMBER IT NOW,
THE ERA OF BIG GOVERNMENT IS
OVER.
THAT WORKED FOR HIM BECAUSE
PEOPLE KNEW THAT FOR THE YEAR
SINCE THE ELECTION, HE HAD BEEN
MOVING STEADILY TO THE RIGHT OR
AT LEAST TO THE CENTER FOR WHEN
HE SAID THOSE WORDS, IT HAS SOME
MEANING.
IT HELPED TO POSITION HIM TO RUN
SUCCESSFULLY FOR REELECTION AND
ALSO I WAS INTERESTED THAT
SENATOR PERDUE WAS TALKING ABOUT
NEWT GINGRICH AND BILL CLINTON.
THAT STATE OF THE UNION SET THAT
UP FOR CLINTON AND GINGRICH BY
THE SUMMER OF 1996 TO DO WELFARE
REFORM TOGETHER, TO BALANCE THE
BUDGET.
IT REALLY CHANGED THE POLITICAL
ATMOSPHERE.
>> Woodruff: IS THERE A
PRECEDENT, MICHAEL BESCHLOSS,
FOR PRESIDENTS WHO HAVE BEEN AT
LOGGERHEADS WITH THE CONGRESS
TURNING THE CORNER AND SETTING
THE STAGE FOR THERE TO BE
REAL -- AN ABILITY TO WORK
TOGETHER?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
1947, HARRY TRUMAN WENT TO GIVE
THE STATE OF THE UNION AFTER HE
LOST CONGRESS TO THE REPUBLICANS
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN 16 YEARS.
HE KNEW THAT THERE WAS A BIG
NECESSITY FOR HIM TO MAKE DEALS
WITH THE REPUBLICANS, TO PREPARE
THE NATION TO FIGHT THE COLD
WAR, AND THE TRY TO GET SOME OF
THE DOMESTIC LAWS HE WANTED.
HE FAILED AT THE LATTER.
>> Woodruff: DO YOU SENSE
AGAIN, FROM STUDIED HISTORY,
STUDIED SO MANY PRESIDENTS, THAT
THERE IS A WILLINGNESS, A WILL
ON THE PART OF THE TWO PARTIES
THAT HAVE BEEN FIGHTING EACH
OTHER FOR WEEK AFTER WEEK, DAY
AFTER DAY, TO COME TOGETHER?
>> I THINK THEY KNOW THAT AN
AWFUL LOT OF AMERICANS WOULD
LIKE TO SEE THAT.
THAT SURELY SHOWS UP IN THE
POLLS.
BUT THERE HAS NOT BEEN MUCH SIGN
OF IT DURING THE LAST MONTH, AND
WE WILL SEE IF THIS SPEECH
CHANGES THE ATMOSPHERE I THINK
RARELY IN HISTORY DOES THAT
HAPPEN.
>> Woodruff: AND THAT'S WHAT I
WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT, TOO.
HOW MUCH DIFFERENCE CAN ONE
SPEECH, ONE GRANTED -- THIS IS A
BIG DEAL, IT'S THE STATE OF THE
UNION, IT'S A WHOLE LOT OF
TRADITION WRAPPED AROUND THIS.
>>
>> SURE.
>> Woodruff: CAN ONE ADDRESS
MAKE A DIFFERENCE?
>> IF PEOPLE HAVE THE FEELING
THAT LURKING WITHIN DONALD TRUMP
HAS BEEN THIS DEEP DESIRE TO
MAKE DEALS WITH THE OTHER SIDE
THAT HAS NOT EXPRESSED ITSELF,
AND HE TALKED ABOUT IT A LOT
DURING THE CAMPAIGN, 2016, A LOT
OF PEOPLE VOTED FOR TRUMP,
BECAUSE THEY SAID I KNOW CHUCK
SCHUMER, I CAN MAKE DEALS WITH
HIM, AND THEY FEEL IN MANY CASES
THAT IT HASN'T BEEN EXPRESSED,
IF WE BEGIN TO SEE SIGNS OF THAT
DONALD TRUMP IN THE WAKE OF THIS
SPEECH, THINGS COULD BEGIN TO
CHANGE.
I'M NOT PREDICTING THAT.
>> Woodruff: WHY NOT?
>> BECAUSE THIS SPEECH WAS
PRECEDED BY AN ENORMOUS
CONFRONTATION, ONE OF THE
BIGGEST IN LEGISLATIVE WHITE
HOUSE RELATIONS HISTORY, THAT
LED TO A SHUTDOWN AND MAY YET
AGAIN.
>> Woodruff: JUST VERY
QUICKLY, YOU HAVE LOOKED AT THE
LANGUAGE THIS PRESIDENT USE, THE
WAY HE COMMUNICATES WITH THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
DO YOU -- HOW MUCH DO YOU EXPECT
HIM TO STAY IN THAT LANE, AND
HOW MUCH MIGHT HE --
>> NOT FOR LONG.
HE DOESN'T ENJOY IT.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN MANY INSTANCES
OF IT.
IF WE DID, THE TIME WE WOULD
HAVE SEEN IT WAS DURING THE
INAUGURATION WHEN EVEN THE MOST
PARTISAN PRESIDENTS GIVE A
UNIFYING SPEECH.
HE WOULD BE FIRST TO SAY HE DID
NOT.
>> Woodruff: MICHAEL
BESCHLOSS, THANK YOU.
>> MY PLEASURE.
>> Woodruff: APPRECIATE IT.
>> Woodruff: NOW, PERSPECTIVE ON
THE RUN-UP TO TONIGHT'S BIG
ADDRESS, FROM OPPOSITE SIDES OF
THE AMERICAN POLITICAL SPECTRUM:
KARINE JEAN-PIERRE IS A SENIOR
ADVISER FOR moveon.org.
AND CHRIS BUSKIRK IS EDITOR OF
THE CONSERVATIVE JOURNAL AND
WEBSITE "AMERICAN GREATNESS."
HELLO TO BOTH OF YOU.
>> HI.
>> Woodruff: GREAT TO HAVE YOU
BATH ON THE PROGRAM.
CHRIS, TO YOU FIRST, CHRIS
BUSKIRK, WHAT DO YOU EXPECT THE
PRESIDENT TO DO TONIGHT?
>> I THINK WHAT THE PRESIDENT
WILL DO TONIGHT IS HE IS GOING
TO DO WHAT HE'S DONE I THINK
PRETTY WELL IN SOME SPEECHES
BEFORE, WHICH IS GOING BACK TO
PROMISES MADE, PROMISES KEPT.
HERE'S WHAT I'VE TALKED ABOUT IN
MY CAMPAIGN, HERE'S WHAT I'VE
ACCOMPLISHED SO FAR, HERE'S WHAT
I STILL NEED TO DO.
HERE WE ARE HALFWAY THROUGH
FIRST TERM.
THIS HAS GOT TO BE THE PIVOT TO
REELECTION, TO TRY TO START TO
SET THE TONE AND SET THE
TRAJECTORY FOR A MESSAGE THAT'S
GOING TO CARRY HIM THROUGH
NOVEMBER OF 2020.
I THINK THAT NEEDS TO BE ONE BIG
UNIFYING THEME THAT SAYS, ON
IMMIGRATION, ON TRADE, ON
FOREIGN POLICY, HOW ARE ALL
THESE THINGS LINKED TOGETHER?
WHAT'S THAT UNIFYING THEME?
I THINK THAT THAT THEME HAS TO
BE HOW DO YOU REBUILD THE MIDDLE
CLASS.
>> Woodruff: THAT'S NUMBER
ONE.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT HE GOING TO
TRY TO DO.
>> Woodruff: IF THAT'S WHAT HE
DOES, KARINE JEAN-PIERRE, HOW IS
THAT RECEIVED BY DEMOCRATS?
>> SO I KNOW THAT IT'S BEEN
REPORTED THAT FROM THE
ADMINISTRATION, FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE THAT THE PRESIDENT IS
GOING TO GIVE A SPEECH ON UNITY,
ON GREATNESS, ON BIPARTISANSHIP,
AND THAT WOULD BE GREAT IF HE
WAS ABLE TO DO THAT, BUT WE HAVE
NOT SEEN THAT FROM THIS
PRESIDENT IN THE PAST NOW GOING
ON THREE YEARS.
AND I JUST DON'T SEE THIS SPEECH
ONLY BECAUSE OF HISTORICAL
LANDMARK TRY OF HIS RECORD BEING
THAT IMPACTFUL.
SO MAYBE, MAYBE HE GETS THERE
AND HE MAKES THE SPEECH, BUT
HOURS LATER, THE MOMENT HE GETS
ON TWITTER, HE STEPS ON IT.
SO IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE.
AND LET'S NOT FORGET, A COUPLE
WEEKS AGO HE ADDRESSED THE
COUNTRY IN DIPLOMATIC RECEPTION
ROOM WHERE HE TALKED ABOUT
IMMIGRATION, AND THAT WAS FILLED
WITH DIVISION.
AND THEN HE DID IT WEEKS PRIOR
THE THAT IN THE OVAL OFFICE
BEHIND THE RESOLUTE DESK.
THAT WAS FILLED WITH DIVISION
AND HATE.
SO I JUST DON'T SEE HOW THAT'S
POSSIBLE COMING FROM THIS
PRESIDENT.
>> Woodruff: IN FACT, CHRIS
BUSKIRK, I HAD A CHANCE TODAY TO
SPEND A LITTLE BIT -- A FEW
MINUTES WITH SPEAKER PELOSI AND
SENATE MINORITY LEADER CHUCK
SCHUMER.
SENATOR CHUCK SCHUMER MADE A
POINT OF SAYING, WE HOPE THE
PRESIDENT WILL APPEAL THE UNITY,
BUT IN THE PAST WHEN HE'S SPOKEN
AT A MOMENT, WHETHER IT'S A
STATE OF THE UNION ADDRESS OR
ANOTHER IMPORTANT SPEECH, HE'S
MADE PROMISES OR MADE
DECLARATIONS THAT HE THEN TURNED
AROUND AND DIDN'T FULFILL.
SO WHAT MAKES YOU CONVINCED THAT
TONIGHT IS GOING TO BE
DIFFERENT.
>> WELL, I THINK PART OF THAT IS
IN THE EYE OF THE BEHOLDER.
WHAT IS UNITY.
THERE'S PART OF IT THAT IS THE
ART OF PERSUASION, WHICH IS TO
TALK ABOUT IT AND TO USE THE
RHETORIC OF UNITY AND TO TALK
ABOUT HOW DO WE -- HOW ARE WE
AMERICANS TOGETHER.
HOW DO WE BILL THINGS TOGETHER,
MAKE THIS A BETTER SOCIETY.
HOW THAT TRANSLATES INTO
PRACTICE IS I THINK WHERE THE
PRESIDENT NEEDS TO BE VERY
CONCRETE.
HE NEEDS THE USE THE RHETORIC
AND SAY, THESE ARE THE POLICIES
WE'LL PURSUE IN MY
ADMINISTRATION THE TRY TO MAKE
THIS A REALITY.
THAT'S WHAT EVERYBODY IS REALLY
LOOKING FOR.
THIS IS A GOOD SPEECH.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO ABOUT
IT.
>> Woodruff: BUT YOU HAVE A
SENSE THAT NOW, CHRIS BUSKIRK,
THE PRESIDENT IS PREPARED TO DO
THAT?
>> I THINK HE HAS TO, AND I
THINK THAT'S WHAT HE'S GOING TO
TRY TO DO.
>> Woodruff: KARINE, YOU'RE
EXPRESSING DOUBT?
>> HE DOESN'T HAVE A
RECORD-OF-THAT, JUDY.
HE HAVE NOT SEEN THAT.
A YEAR AGO HE TALKED ABOUT
UNITY.
MONTHS LATER WE GOT THE ZERO
POLICY SITUATION WHERE CHILDREN
OF UNDOCUMENTED IMMIGRANTS WERE
BEING RIPPED AWAY FROM THEIR
PARENTS.
THAT WAS DEVASTATEING TO SEE.
NOW WE'RE HEARING MANY OF THEM
WILL NEVER BE REUNITED.
THE YEAR BEFORE THAT IN 2017, IN
THE JOINT ADDRESS, THE SAME
THING, AND WHAT DID WE SEE?
WE HEARD ABOUT CHARLOTTESVILLE.
AND WHAT DID HE DO THERE?
HE SAID VERY FINE PEOPLE ON BOTH
SIDES.
I JUST DON'T SEE IT.
>> Woodruff: WHEN YOU HEAR
THIS, CHRIS BUSKIRK, WHAT DO YOU
THINK?
>> I THINK THAT UNITY DOES NOT
MEAN AGREEMENT ON EVERYTHING.
AND THAT'S OKAY.
THAT'S WHAT POLITICS IS FOR.
I THINK WHAT UNITY MEANS IS NOT
THAT DONALD TRUMP SAYS TO
SPEAKER PELOSI, WHATEVER YOU
WANT, THAT'S FINE.
I THINK WHAT IT MEANS IS HOW DO
WE IDENTIFY THE PROBLEMS THE
COUNTRY FACES AND HOW DO WE WORK
TOGETHER, AND WE CAN DISAGREE ON
OTHER THINGS, BUT LET'S DO THAT
IN A WAY WHERE WE AT LEAST SET
THE TABLE ON COMMON GOALS.
>> Brangham: AND I GUESS THE
FLIP SIDE OF THAT QUESTION
KARINE JEAN-PIERRE, ARE
DEMOCRATS, ARE PEOPLE LIKE YOU,
WHO WORK HARD FOR THE
ORGANIZATIONS THAT OPPOSE SO
MUCH OF THE PRESIDENT'S POLICIES
RUSSIA YOU WILLING TO GIVE THE
PRESIDENT THE BENEFIT OF THE
DOUBT.
>> THERE ARE THINGS THAT WE CAN
WORK ON THAT'S BIPARTISAN, WHICH
IS DACA, INFRASTRUCTURE,
IMMIGRATION FOR YOUNG
UNDOCUMENTED FOLKS WHO CAME
HERE, YOU KNOW, WITH THEIR
PARENTS WHEN THEY WERE REALLY
YOUNG.
AND THERE IS ALSO THE CRIMINAL
JUSTICE.
RIGHT?
THAT WAS DONE IN A BIPARTISAN
WAY.
IT WAS A FIRST STEP.
THERE IS MORE TO BE DONE.
THE PROBLEM IS, AND WHAT WE SAID
EARLIER, HE DECLARES THINGS IN
HIS SPEECH, BUT THEN HE DOESN'T
STICK TO THEM.
AND I THINK DEMOCRATS ARE READY
TO WORK ON THOSE THINGS, BUT HE
DOESN'T STICK TO IT.
>> Woodruff: I WANT TO LOOK AT
THIS, STEP BACK A LITTLE BIT,
CHRIS BUSKIRK, BECAUSE PART OF
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE IS MANY OF
THE PEOPLE WHO SUPPORT THE
PRESIDENT DON'T SEEM TO WANT HIM
TO COOPERATE WITH THE OTHER SIDE
AND, KARINE, I THINK YOU CAN SAY
THAT ABOUT A NUMBER OF
PROGRESSIVE LIBERAL DEMOCRATS
WHO DON'T WANT TO SEE THEIR
PARTY COOPERATE.
WHAT ABOUT THAT, CHRIS?
>> THE BEST WAY FOR ME AT LEAST
TO THINK ABOUT IT IS TO USE A
CON EXREET ILLUSTRATION.
SO YOU THINK ABOUT THE
IMMIGRATION ISSUE.
THIS IS A PLACE WHERE PEOPLE
LIKE SPEAKER PELOSI AND MINORITY
LEADER CHUCK SCHUMER, TEN YEARS
AGO, 12 YEARS AGO, WE NEED A
WALL, WE NEED BOARDER SECURITY.
I THINK WHAT THE PRESIDENT NEEDS
TO DO IS EXPLAIN WHY THAT'S
IMPORTANT AND HOW THAT IS
SOMETHING THAT PROTECTS, HOW
BORDER SECURITY PROTECTS WORKING
FAMILIES.
AMERICAN WORKING FAMILIES.
WHY?
BECAUSE IT PROTECTS THEIR MOST
VALUABLE ASSET, WHICH IS THEIR
ASYMMETRIC ACCESS TO THE
AMERICAN LABOR MARKET.
MAKE THAT ARGUMENT MAYBE IN A
MORE --
>> Woodruff: IN OTHER WORDS,
IMMIGRANTS TAKE JOBS AWAY FROM
YOU?
>> TAKE JOBS AWAY, LOWER WAGE,
MORE SUPPLY LOWERS PRICES.
THAT'S BASIC.
YOU EXPLAIN THAT TO PEOPLE AND
SAY, THIS IS WHY IMMIGRATION IS
IMPORTANT TO ME.
THIS IS WHY TRADE POLICY IS
I WANT MIDDLE-INCOME FAMILIES TO
BE SECURE ECONOMICALLY, AND THEY
NEED TO BE ABLE TO PROSPER.
>> Woodruff: KARINE, THE FLIP
SIDE, LIBERAL DEMOCRATS DON'T
WANT THEIR PARTY LEADERS TO WORK
TOGETHER WITH THE PRESIDENT.
>> WELL, THEY WANT DEMOCRATS, IN
PARTICULAR IN THE HOUSE NOW THAT
IT'S THE MAJORITY, TO HOLD THIS
PRESIDENT ACCOUNTABLE.
THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS THAT
WE TOOK BACK THE HOUSE.
SO THAT'S REALLY IMPORTANT.
THAT LOOKS IN VERY DIFFERENT
WAYS.
THAT'S LOOKING AT THE MUELLER
REPORT.
IT'S ALSO LOOKING AT CHILDREN
BEING SEPARATED AT THE BORDER.
PUERTO RICO, 3,000 PEOPLE DIED.
BUT THEY ALSO WANT TO SEE
DEMOCRATS MOVING THE COUNTRY
FORWARD, RIGHT?
AND THEY'VE DONE THAT WITH
VOTING RIGHTS AND DEALING WITH
CORRUPTION, AND SO THESE ARE
THINGS THEY ACTUALLY WANT TO
SEE, BUT WE NEED POLITICIANS ON
THE OTHER SIDE TO ALSO BE IN
THERE WITH US, TOO.
>> Woodruff: ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL HAVE CHANCE TO TALK ABOUT
ALL THIS AGAIN LATER TONIGHT
WHEN WE'VE HEARD WHAT THE
PRESIDENT HAS TO SAY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, KARINE
JEAN-PIERRE, CHRIS BUSKIRK.
THANK YOU.
>> Woodruff: FOR A ROUNDUP OF
TODAY'S OTHER MAJOR HEADLINES,
HERE'S AMNA NAWAZ.
>> Nawaz: IN THE NON STATE OF
THE UNION NEWS THIS DAY, THE
WHITE HOUSE PLAYED DOWN A
FEDERAL SUBPOENA SEEKING A HOST
OF DOCUMENTS FROM PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S INAUGURAL COMMITTEE.
FEDERAL PROSECUTORS IN NEW YORK
ARE INVESTIGATING WHO GAVE THE
MONEY AND WHAT THEY MIGHT HAVE
RECEIVED IN RETURN.
WHITE HOUSE SPOKESWOMAN SARAH
SANDERS CALLED IT "HYSTERIA"
OVER THE FACT THAT MR. TRUMP WAS
ELECTED.
>> THIS DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING TO
DO WITH THE WHITE HOUSE AND I
THINK THE BIGGEST FOCUS AND THE
THING THAT MOST AMERICANS CARE
ABOUT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH THE
INAUGURAL AND IT HAS EVERYTHING
TO DO WITH WHAT THE PATH FORWARD
LOOKS LIKE.
>> Nawaz: INVESTIGATORS ARE ALSO
LOOKING INTO WHETHER ANY FOREIGN
DONORS ILLEGALLY CONTRIBUTED TO
THE INAUGURAL COMMITTEE.
ONE OF PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
JUDICIAL NOMINEES VOICED REGRETS
TODAY FOR HER PAST STATEMENTS ON
RAPE, RACE AND EQUAL RIGHTS.
NEOMI RAO APPEARED BEFORE THE
SENATE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE.
SENATORS ON BOTH SIDES
CRITICIZED HER FOR WRITING, IN
COLLEGE, THAT WOMEN BEAR SOME
BLAME IF THEY'RE SEXUALLY
ASSAULTED WHILE INTOXICATED.
>> TO BE HONEST LOOKING BACK AT
SOME OF THOSE WRITINGS AND RE-
READING THEM I CRINGE AT SOME OF
THE LANGUAGE THAT I USED.
I'VE HAD A LOT OF EXPERIENCE
SINCE THAT TIME WRITING IN
COLLEGE AND I DON'T THINK I
WOULD EXPRESS MYSELF IN THE SAME
WAY THESE ARE HORRIBLE CRIMES
AND I WOULDN'T WRITE ANYTHING
THAT WOULD IMPLY TO BLAME A
VICTIM OR MAKE IT LESS LIKELY
FOR A VICTIM TO COME FORWARD.
>> Nawaz: RAO CURRENTLY LEADS
THE WHITE HOUSE OFFICE
OVERSEEING DEREGULATION.
IF CONFIRMED, SHE'D TAKE THE
FEDERAL APPEALS COURT SEAT HELD
BY BRETT KAVANAUGH, BEFORE HE
JOINED THE SUPREME COURT.
OVERSEAS, IN AFGHANISTAN,
TALIBAN ATTACKS KILLED NEARLY 50
PEOPLE IN TWO NORTHERN
PROVINCES.
A PRE-DAWN RAID KILLED 26
SOLDIERS AND POLICE AT AN ARMY
BASE IN KUNDUZ PROVINCE, ON THE
OUTSKIRTS OF KUNDUZ CITY.
ATTACKS IN NEIGHBORING PROVINCES
KILLED 21 OTHERS.
THE TALIBAN HAVE KEPT UP THEIR
OFFENSIVE, EVEN AMID EARLY
STAGES OF PEACE TALKS WITH THE
U.S.
THE TOP U.S. COMMANDER IN THE
MIDDLE EAST SAYS PRESIDENT TRUMP
DID NOT TALK TO HIM BEFORE
ANNOUNCING AMERICAN FORCES WILL
WITHDRAW FROM SYRIA.
ARMY GENERAL JOSEPH VOTEL
TESTIFIED AT A SENATE HEARING
TODAY, AND WAS QUESTIONED BY
MAINE SENATOR ANGUS KING.
>> GENERAL, WERE YOU AWARE OF
THE PRESIDENT'S INTENTION TO
ORDER THE WITHDRAWAL OF TROOPS
FROM SYRIA BEFORE THAT WAS
PUBLICLY ANNOUNCED?
>> I WAS NOT AWARE OF THE
SPECIFIC ANNOUNCEMENT.
CERTAINLY WE ARE AWARE THAT HE
HAD EXPRESSED A DESIRE AND A
INTENT IN THE PAST TO DEPART
IRAQ-- TO DEPART SYRIA.
>> SO YOU WERE NOT CONSULTED
BEFORE THAT DECISION WAS MADE?
>> WE WERE NOT-- I WAS NOT
CONSULTED
>> Nawaz: VOTEL'S REMARKS CAME A
DAY AFTER THE DEFENSE DEPARTMENT
WARNED THAT ISLAMIC STATE
FIGHTERS COULD RE-SURGE IN SYRIA
AFTER THE U.S. WITHDRAWS.
POPE FRANCIS HAS CELEBRATED THE
FIRST-EVER PAPAL MASS ON THE
ARABIAN PENINSULA.
SOME 180,000 PEOPLE GATHERED
TODAY AT A SPORTS STADIUM IN ABU
DHABI, CAPITAL OF THE UNITED
ARAB EMIRATES.
FRANCIS PREACHED HUMILITY, IN
ONE OF THE WORLD'S RICHEST
NATIONS.
>> ( translated ): FOR JESUS, ON
THE OTHER HAND, BLESSED ARE THE
POOR, THE MEEK, THOSE WHO REMAIN
JUST EVEN AT THE COST OF
APPEARING IN A BAD LIGHT, THOSE
WHO ARE PERSECUTED.
HE TAUGHT US THAT GREATNESS IS
NOT FOUND IN HAVING BUT RATHER
IN GIVING.
>> Nawaz: LATER, THE POPE
ACKNOWLEDGED, FOR THE FIRST
TIME, THE SCANDAL OF PRIESTS
SEXUALLY ABUSING NUNS.
HE SAID HE IS COMMITTED TO
FIGHTING THE PROBLEM.
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE IN ASIA AND
AROUND THE WORLD MARKED THE
LUNAR NEW YEAR TODAY.
IN TAIWAN, THOUSANDS GATHERED TO
PRAY AT A BUDDHIST TEMPLE.
IN THE PHILIPPINES, PEOPLE
BOUGHT ROASTED PIG, A DELICACY,
TO USHER IN THE "YEAR OF THE
PIG."
AND ALL ACROSS CHINA, CROWDS
VISITED TEMPLES AND TOOK PART IN
FESTIVALS.
BACK IN THIS COUNTRY, TEXAS
LAWMAKERS COMPLAINED TODAY THE
STATE STILL HAS NOT RECEIVED
HURRICANE "HARVEY" RECOVERY
FUNDS.
THE STORM DID MAJOR DAMAGE
IN 2017, AND LAST FEBRUARY,
CONGRESS EARMARKED SOME $4.4
BILLION FOR TEXAS, BUT NO GRANTS
HAVE ACTUALLY BEEN MADE.
THE STATE'S REPUBLICAN SENATORS,
PLUS 10 HOUSE MEMBERS FROM BOTH
PARTIES, SAY FEDERAL BUDGET
BUREAUCRACY IS STANDING IN THE
WAY.
AN OUTSPOKEN CRITIC OF THE WORLD
BANK, DAVID MALPASS, LOOKS LIKE
HE'LL BE PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
CHOICE TO LEAD THE AGENCY.
IT WAS WIDELY REPORTED TODAY
THAT THE PRESIDENT WILL NOMINATE
HIM THIS WEEK.
THE WORLD BANK PROVIDES LOANS
FOR PROJECTS AROUND THE WORLD,
BUT MALPASS HAS COMPLAINED IT IS
PILING UP DEBT WITHOUT RESULTS.
ALSO TODAY, ANDREW WHEELER WON A
SENATE COMMITTEE'S APPROVAL TO
BE HEAD OF THE E.P.A.
HIS NOMINATION NOW GOES TO THE
FULL SENATE.
AND, ON WALL STREET, A SERIES OF
STRONG EARNINGS REPORTS GAVE
STOCKS ANOTHER BOOST.
THE DOW JONES INDUSTRIAL AVERAGE
GAINED 172 POINTS TO CLOSE AT
25,411.
THE NASDAQ ROSE 54 POINTS, AND
THE S&P 500 ADDED 12.
STILL TO COME ON THE NEWSHOUR:
REACTION TO THE PRESIDENT'S
COMMENTS THAT THE U.S. WILL USE
A BASE IN IRAQ TO KEEP EYES ON
IRAN.
A RIGOROUS PROGRAM PREPARES
BLACK UNDERGRADUATES TO GO ON TO
MEDICAL SCHOOL.
PLUS, ESSAYIST RACHEL KAADZI
GHANSAH GIVES HER BRIEF BUT
SPECTACULAR TAKE ON
FEARLESSNESS.
>> Woodruff: AS WE REPORTED, THE
TOP U.S. MILITARY COMMANDER FOR
THE MIDDLE EAST WAS ON CAPITOL
HILL TODAY.
IN ADDITION TO THE FIGHT AGAINST
ISIS, HE WAS ASKED ABOUT RECENT
COMMENTS BY PRESIDENT TRUMP
SUGGESTING AMERICAN TROOPS IN
IRAQ COULD SHIFT THEIR MISSION.
AND AS NICK SCHIFRIN REPORTS,
THOSE COMMENTS ABOUT U.S. TROOPS
WATCHING IRAN, HAVE SPARKED DEEP
CONCERN IN IRAQ.
>> Schifrin: NEAR THE IRAQI-
SYRIAN BORDER, AN IRAQI SOLDIER,
AND HIS AMERICAN ADVISOR, LINE
UP ARTILLERY TO STRIKE ISIS.
OUTSIDE BAGHAD, U.S. SPECIAL
OPERATIONS FORCES TRAIN IRAQ'S
ELITE COUNTER-TERRORISM SERVICE.
AND IRAQI SOLDIERS LEARN TO FIRE
AMERICAN RIFLES, WITH OVERSIGHT
FROM ANTI-ISIS COALITION TROOPS.
THESE SCENES OF PARTNERSHIP,
FILMED BY THE U.S. MILITARY OVER
THE LAST YEAR, SHOW WHAT IRAQ
HAS INVITED THE U.S. TO DO.
5200 U.S. TROOPS TRAIN IRAQI
SECURITY FORCES, AND TARGET ISIS
FIGHTERS WHO LOST TERRITORY, BUT
RESUMED INSURGENT TACTICS.
BUT THIS WEEKEND, PRESIDENT
TRUMP TOLD CBS' MARGARET BRENNAN
THE MISSION SHOULD EXPAND.
>> AND ONE OF THE REASONS I WANT
TO KEEP IT IS BECAUSE I WANT TO
BE LOOKING A LITTLE BIT AT IRAN
BECAUSE IRAN IS A REAL PROBLEM.
>> WHOA, THAT'S NEWS.
YOU'RE KEEPING TROOPS IN IRAQ
BECAUSE YOU WANT TO BE ABLE TO
STRIKE IN IRAN?
>> NO, BECAUSE I WANT TO BE ABLE
TO WATCH IRAN.
ALL I WANT TO DO IS BE ABLE TO
WATCH.
>> Schifrin: BUT EVEN WATCHING
IRAN EXCEEDS THE TASKS IRAQ HAS
APPROVED.
HE CRITICIZED PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> ( TRANSLATED ): I DON'T THINK
SUCH STATEMENTS ARE USEFUL.
IN FACT, THEY WON'T HELP MUCH.
I HOPE HE WOULD BACK DOWN FROM
THERE.
>> A N A STATEMENT, FIRST DEPUTY
SPEAKER REPEATED A VOW THAT
PARLIAMENT WOULD PASS A LAW
TERMINATING THE SECURITY
AGREEMENT WITH AMERICA, IN
ADDITION TO ENDING THE PRESENCE
OF AMERICAN MILITARY TRAINERS
AND ADVISERS AND FORT PIERCERS
ON IRAQI SOIL.
IN A LEBANON-BASED TV NETWORK ON
SUNDAY, A IRANIAN-BACKED
SPOKESMAN HINTED MILITIAS HAD
THE CAPACITY TO EVICT THE U.S.
>> ( TRANSLATED ): ALL OF OUR
OPTIONS ARE OPEN IN FRONT OF US.
WE HAVE THE ABILITY AND
RESOURCES TO EXECUTE THEM.
>> WHAT THE PRESIDENT REMARKS
HAVE DONE IS MAKE IT MORE
DIFFICULT FOR EVEN AMERICA'S
CLOSEST ALLIES IN THE IRAQI
POLITICAL CLASS TO CONTINUE TO
ADVOCATE FOR THE AMERICAN
PRESENCE IN IRAQ.
>> Schifrin: FEISAL ISTRABADI IS
A FORMER IRAQI DIPLOMAT AND
DIRECTS INDIANA UNIVERSITY'S
CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF THE
MIDDLE EAST.
THE IRAQI PARLIAMENT WAS ALREADY
DEBATING A BILL THAT WOULD EVICT
THE U.S., IN RESPONSE TO
THAT MOMENTUM WILL INCREASE AND
PUT PRESSURE ON PRIME MINISTER
ADIL ABDUL MAHDI, WHO LEADS A
GOVERNMENT CONSIDERED
TECHNICALLY CAPABLE, BUT HAS NO
NATURAL CONSTITUENCY.
>> HE WAS TURNED TO BY THE
POLITICAL PARTIES IN PARLIAMENT
AND ASKED TO FORM A GOVERNMENT.
HE IS IN THAT SENSE A RELATIVELY
WEAK PRIME MINISTER.
YOU DON'T WANT THE PRIME
MINISTER IN A POLITICAL BATTLE
WITH PARLIAMENT BECAUSE IN THE
IRAQI SYSTEM, THE PRIME MINSTER
WILL ALWAYS LOSE.
>> Schifrin: TODAY, THE TOP
COMMANDER IN THE MIDDLE EAST
TRIED TO REASSURE THAT THE U.S.
RESPECTED IRAQI WISHES.
>> OUR MILITARY MISSION ON THE
GROUND REMAINS VERY FOCUSED ON
THE REASON THAT THE GOVERNMENT
OF IRAQ ASKED US TO COME THERE.
>> Schifrin: AND HE SUGGESTED
THE PRESIDENT'S COMMENTS HAD NOT
BECOME A MILITARY ORDER.
VIRGINIA SENATOR TIM KAINE:
>> AS FAR AS YOU KNOW THERE'S
NOT A CHANGE IN THE DEFINITION
OF THE MISSION, AT LEAST AS FAR
AS THE PENTAGON IS CONCERNED?
>> I HAVE NO ADDITIONAL TASKS
THAT HAVE BEEN GIVEN TO ME WITH
REGARD TO THAT.
>> IF THE U.S. WERE TO CHANGE
ITS DEFINITION OF THE MISSION IN
IRAQ, TO BE A MISSION ABOUT
WATCHING IRAN, WOULDN'T IT BE
PRETTY IMPORTANT TO HAVE IRAQ
AGREE THAT THAT WOULD BE THE
FOCUS OF THE MISSION IF WE WERE
TO BE HAVING TROOPS IN THEIR
COUNTRY TO CARRY OUT SUCH A
MISSION?
>> SENATOR, WE ARE IN IRAQ AT
THE INVITATION OF THE
GOVERNMENT, SO YES, I WOULD
AGREE.
>> Schifrin: ABBAS KADHIM IS
FORMER IRAQI DIPLOMAT AND LEADS
THE ATLANTIC COUNCIL'S IRAQ
INITIATIVE.
HE SAYS PRESIDENT TRUMP'S ORDER
IRAN SAYS THEY DO NOW USE THE
IRAQ I CAN CONSTITUTION TO ARGUE
AGAINST THE U.S. PRESENCE,
BECAUSE IT REQUIRES IRAQ TO
ADHERE TO THE PRINCIPLE OF
NON-INTERFERENCE WITH OTHER
STATES.
>> IRAN HAS MORE FRIENDS INSIDE
IRAQI PARLIAMENT AND ALSO INSIDE
THE GOVERNMENT AND INSIDE EVEN
THE PUBLIC, AND THESE FRIENDS
ARE WILLING TO INDULGE IRAN.
BEFORE SUNDAY THEY DID NOT HAVE
THE VOTES.
NOW I AM TOLD BY SOME PARLIAMENT
MEMBERS THAT THEY HAVE THE VOTES
AT LEAST TO HAVE IT PASS THROUGH
FIRST READING.
THAT IS MAJOR SHIFT.
>>
>> Schifrin: IRAQI LEADERS SAY
THEY KNEW ALL ALONG U.S. TROOPS
IN IRAQ WERE LIKELY CONDUCTING
EXTRA MISSIONS, EVEN WATCHING
IRAN.
BUT UNTIL SUNDAY, THAT WASN'T
MADE PUBLIC.
>> THAT VEIL OF PLAUSIBLE
DENIABILITY, OR WILLFUL
IGNORANCE, WHATEVER YOU WANT TO
CALL IT, THAT'S BEEN LIFTED.
THE PRESIDENT HAS ANNOUNCED WHAT
HIS AGENDA ACTUALLY IS.
>> Schifrin: AND THAT MEANS
THERE WILL BE A FIGHT OVER U.S.
FOR THE PBS NEWSHOUR, I'M NICK
SCHIFRIN.
>> Woodruff: WHILE VIRGINIA
GOVERNOR RALPH NORTHAM WEIGHS
WHETHER TO RESIGN, REACTION AND
ANGER KEEPS BUILDING OVER THE
RACIST PHOTO IN HIS MEDICAL
SCHOOL YEARBOOK.
ONE IMPORTANT PART OF THAT IS
HOW IT SERVES AS A REMINDER OF
RACISM IN MEDICINE HISTORICALLY.
WE'VE REPORTED ON THE IMPORTANCE
OF TRAINING MORE AFRICAN-
AMERICANS TO BECOME DOCTORS.
AND TONIGHT WE HAVE A SECOND
LOOK AT A STORY ON XAVIER
UNIVERSITY, A SMALL HISTORICALLY
BLACK COLLEGE THAT IS HELPING TO
LEAD THE WAY.
HARI SREENIVASAN REPORTS ON WHAT
SETS THE SCHOOL APART FOR OUR
EDUCATION SERIES, "MAKING THE
GRADE."
>> LET'S START WITH GLYCOLYSIS.
>> Sreenivasan: ON THE CAMPUS OF
XAVIER UNIVERSITY, 18-YEAR-OLD
CHRIS WEBB LEADS A BIOLOGY
REVIEW THE NIGHT BEFORE A MAJOR
TEST.
>> ALL YOU REALLY NEED TO KNOW.
>> Sreenivasan: WEBB IS HELPING
FELLOW FRESHMAN WHO, LIKE HIM,
ARE ENROLLED IN A RIGOROUS PRE-
MEDICAL PROGRAM.
>> I WANT THEM TO DO AS BEST AS
THEY CAN.
>> Sreenivasan: THE SCENE IS
FAMILIAR ONE ON THE CAMPUS OF
XAVIER, AN HISTORICALLY BLACK
COLLEGE IN THE HEART OF NEW
ORLEANS.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK OF AEROBIC
RESPIRATION?
>> Sreenivasan: STUDENTS QUIZ
EACH OTHER ON MATERIAL FROM
TOUGH SCIENCE CLASSES, THE KIND
OF COURSES THAT OFTEN WEED OUT
PREMEDICAL STUDENTS.
>> I DON'T WANT THEM TO DO
BETTER THAN ME, BUT WHEN THEY
DO, THAT JUST MAKES ME REALIZE,
OKAY, THIS COMPETITION IS REALLY
SERIOUS.
WHILE WE'RE HAVING FUN WITH IT,
IT'S ALSO VERY REAL.
>> Sreenivasan: WITH A STUDENT
POPULATION OF ONLY 3,000, XAVIER
UNIVERSITY MANAGES TO GRADUATE
MORE AFRICAN AMERICANS WHO GO ON
TO BECOME MEDICAL DOCTORS THAN
ANY OTHER UNDERGRADUATE
INSTITUTION IN THE COUNTRY,
INCLUDING IVY LEAGUES COLLEGES
AND ELITE PUBLIC UNIVERSITIES.
THAT NUMBER IS EVEN MORE
STRIKING GIVEN A DROP IN BLACK
MALES APPLYING TO MEDICAL
SCHOOLS.
ACCORDING TO A RECENT REPORT
FROM THE ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN
MEDICAL COLLEGES, FEWER BLACK
MALES ARE APPLYING TO MEDICAL
SCHOOLS NOW THAN IN 1978.
REYNOLD VERRET IS XAVIER'S
PRESIDENT.
>> WE DO NOT COMPETE TO SAY WHO
IS BETTER.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE A
RELAY RACE, THE GOAL IS TO
FINISH TOGETHER. SO OUR STUDENTS
ARE TRULY EMBRACING AND
ENCOURAGING EACH OTHER TO
ACHIEVE.
>> Sreenivasan: THAT TURNS ON
ITS HEAD TRADITIONAL PRE-MED
PROGRAMS.
>> OH, YES, IT DOES, IT DOES.
>> Sreenivasan: WHICH IS LOOK TO
THE LEFT, LOOK TO THE RIGHT.
>> ONE OF YOU IS GONE, YES.
WE WANT TO GET THROUGH BECAUSE
THE COMPETITION IS ACTUALLY
AFTER WE LEAVE XAVIER, NOT HERE.
THE POINT IS TO GET OUT THERE
TOGETHER.
>> Sreenivasan: CALL IT
COMPETITIVE COLLABORATION.
HEAD OF STUDENT ADVISING QUO
VADIS WEBSTER.
>> AT SOME SCHOOLS YOU SAY,
"LOOK TO YOUR LEFT, LOOK TO YOUR
RIGHT, THIS PERSON MAY NOT BE
HERE."
HERE, WE SAY, "LOOK TO YOUR
LEFT, LOOK TO YOUR RIGHT, YOU
BETTER HELP THE PERSON NEXT TO
YOU SO THAT WE CAN ALL MAKE IT."
>> Sreenivasan: THE INTENSE
STUDENT ADVISING STARTS EARLY.
INCOMING FRESHMAN BEGIN CRAFTING
MEDICAL SCHOOL APPLICATIONS EVEN
BEFORE THEIR FIRST DAY AS AN
UNDERGRADUATE.
>> BEFORE CLASSES START, WE GO
OVER A DIFFERENT ASPECT OF THE
PROCESS OF PREPARING A
COMPETITIVE APPLICATION TO
MEDICAL SCHOOL.
>> Sreenivasan: YOU'RE STARTING
BEFORE THEY ACTUALLY WALK IN THE
DOOR.
>> HAVE TO.
YU NEED SIX SEMESTERS AT LEAST,
BECAUSE THAT'S SIX SEMESTERS
BEFORE YOU APPLY.
YOU NEED EVERY LAST ONE OF THOSE
SEMESTERS AND SUMMERS TO PUT
INTO MAKING YOURSELF A
COMPETITIVE APPLICATION.
>> Sreenivasan: THE PREMED
PROGRAM ALSO RELIES HEAVILY ON
TUTORING BY UPPERCLASSMEN.
BRADLEY DUNN, SAYS HE COULD NOT
HAVE MADE IT THROUGH HIS FIRST
SEMESTER WITHOUT THE FREE
TUTORING CENTER.
DUNN'S STUDENT TUTOR, CHINYERE
JONES.
>> BASICALLY WHENEVER HE HAD A
BREAK HE WAS IN THE TUTORING
CENTER.
I WAS LIKE, JEEZ.
>> Sreenivasan: DUNN BELIEVES
STUDENTS HELPING STUDENTS COMES
IN PART FROM SHARED EXPERIENCES
ABOUT RACE.
>> THEY UNDERSTAND THE PLIGHT OF
AFRICAN AMERICANS.
IT'S MORE RELATABLE, AND IT'S
MORE INTIMATE, AND WE ALL KNOW
THE PITFALLS THAT WE MAY FACE AS
PEOPLE, AND TOGETHER, WE'RE A
UNIT.
AND I'M ACTUALLY TAKING PRIDE IN
THAT BLACKNESS.
>> Sreenivasan: RACE IS ALSO AN
IMPORTANT FACTOR FOR CHRIS WEBB,
WHO CHOSE XAVIER OVER FULL
SCHOLARSHIPS TO OTHER
UNIVERSITIES, INCLUDING
VANDERBILT AND TULANE.
>> SEEING PEOPLE THAT LOOK LIKE
ME, AND GETTING TO MED SCHOOL,
AND THROUGH MED SCHOOL, IT
MOTIVATES ME MORE COMPETING WITH
PEOPLE THAT ARE LIKE ME.
>> Sreenivasan: ONE OF THOSE
ROLE MODELS IS DR. RYAN JUPITER.
JUPITER IS A RESIDENT DOCTOR IN
THE EMERGENCY DEPARTMENT OF NEW
ORLEANS UNIVERSITY MEDICAL
CENTER.
AN XAVIER ALUMNI, HE VISITS
CAMPUS REGULARLY TO TELL
STUDENTS HIS OWN STORY AS THE
FIRST IN HIS FAMILY TO GO TO
COLLEGE.
>> I WANTED TO MAKE SURE THAT I
COULD LOOK LIKE I DO AND STILL
BE ABLE TO BECOME WHAT I WANT TO
BE.
>> Sreenivasan: HOW IMPORTANT IS
THAT?
DO YOU THINK THAT YOUNG BLACK
MEN DON'T SEE THAT ENOUGH?
>> DEFINITELY.
I DON'T THINK THEY DO AT ALL.
IT'S ALSO A LONG JOURNEY, AND
WHEN YOU SEE OTHER PEOPLE WHO
PUT IN THE TIME AND THE WORK AND
SEE THE RESULTS OF IT, THEN IT
KIND OF HELPS WITH THE LONG
STRUGGLE THAT IT TAKES.
>> Sreenivasan: WHEN WE MET DR.
JUPITER, HE HAD HIS MONOGRAMMED
JACKET ON, WHICH HE TOOK OFF FOR
OUR INTERVIEW.
BUT HE EXPLAINED HOW HE NORMALLY
WEARS THE JACKET IN THE HOSPITAL
BECAUSE IT IS ONE MORE VISUAL
CUE TO PATIENTS THAT HE IS A
PHYSICIAN, SOMETHING HE SAYS
PEOPLE DON'T ALWAYS EXPECT FROM
A YOUNG BLACK MALE.
HAVE YOU BEEN MISTAKEN FOR
SOMETHING OTHER THAN A DOCTOR?
>> ALL THE TIME.
IT HAPPENS.
I DON'T THINK IT'S INTENTIONAL,
OR WOULD LIKE TO THINK IT'S NOT
INTENTIONAL, BUT IT'S VERY RARE
THAT YOU CAN WALK INTO A ROOM AS
A PATIENT, AND WHEN YOU SEE A
BLACK, AFRICAN-AMERICAN MALE
WITH DREADS IN HIS HAIR AND, YOU
KNOW, THAT THIS IS MY DOCTOR
UNTIL YOU FORMALLY INTRODUCE
YOURSELF.
OR, YOU LOOK AT THE COMMENTS,
"NURSE," OR "CAN YOU GET THIS
FOR ME," OR "ARE YOU HERE TO
CLEAN THE ROOM," SO TO SPEAK.
THOSE THINGS HAVE ALL, HAVE ALL
HAPPENED.
>> Sreenivasan: STUDENTS AT
XAVIER HOPE TO CHANGE THOSE
STEREOTYPES.
>> WE ALL RECOGNIZE THAT PEOPLE
DON'T TRULY SEE US FOR WHO WE
ARE.
WE USE THAT TO MOTIVATE
OURSELVES, AND TO TRY TO SHOW
PEOPLE WE'RE A LOT MORE THAN
WHAT YOU TAKE US FOR.
>> AS AFRICAN-AMERICANS, WE'RE
KNOWN TO BE GREAT IN SPORTS, BUT
WE CAN BE SO MUCH GREATER IN
OTHER AREAS, AND I JUST FEEL
LIKE WE NEED TO BE MORE
REPRESENTED.
>> Sreenivasan: THERE IS A
BRIGHT SPOT FOR MINORITY TRENDS
IN THE FIELD.
THE NUMBER OF BLACK WOMEN
APPLYING TO MEDICAL SCHOOL IS ON
THE RISE.
>> BLACK WOMEN HAVE SOMETHING TO
PROVE.
>> Sreenivasan: XAVIER SOPHOMORE
RACHELS HITCHENS HAS ALREADY
BEEN ACCEPTED INTO THE
UNIVERSITY OF ROCHESTER MEDICAL
SCHOOL.
>> WE'VE BEEN OBJECTIFIED FOR SO
MANY YEARS.
WE HAVE TO PROVE THAT WE CAN BE
MORE THAN VIDEO DANCERS, WE CAN
ACTUALLY USE OUR BRAIN AND I
THINK THAT'S THE MOTIVATING
FORCE THAT'S DEEP DOWN WITHIN SO
MANY BLACK WOMEN LIKE MYSELF.
>> Sreenivasan: AND LIKE
HITCHENS, THE STUDENTS WE SPOKE
TO AT THIS SMALL NEW ORLEANS
COLLEGE HAD BIG PLANS.
>> I WANT TO BE AN ORTHOPEDIC
SURGEON.
>> I WANT TO BE A PEDIATRIC
CARDIOLOGIST.
>> I WANT TO BE A RURAL FAMILY
PRACTICE PHYSICIAN.
>> Sreenivasan: PAVING THE WAY
FOR ANOTHER GENERATION OF
AFRICAN AMERICAN DOCTORS.
IN NEW ORLEANS FOR THE PBS
NEWSHOUR, I'M HARI SREENIVASAN.
>> Woodruff: FINALLY, TONIGHT, A
GENEROUS JOURNALISM PRIZE WAS
AWARDED TODAY BY THE HEISING-
SIMONS FOUNDATION.
THE AMERICAN MOSAIC PRIZE IS
GIVEN TO TWO FREELANCE
JOURNALISTS FOR LONG FORM
REPORTING THAT HIGHLIGHTS
UNDERREPRESENTED GROUPS IN THE
AMERICAN LANDSCAPE.
THE TWO RECIPIENTS THIS YEAR ARE
ABE STREEP AND RACHEL KAADZI
GHANSAH, WHOSE WORK ALSO
RECEIVED THE PULITZER PRICE LAST
YEAR.
GHANSAH WAS FEATURED IN OUR
BRIEF BUT SPECTACULAR SERIES IN
2016, AND SO WE BRING THAT TO
YOU AGAIN, AND CONGRATULATE HER
AND ABE STREEP FOR THIS HONOR,
AND WITH ENCOURAGEMENT TO
CONTINUE DOING IMPORTANT
JOURNALISM.
>> I LIKE WRITING ABOUT PEOPLE
WHO LOOK LIKE ME AND THE PEOPLE
I KNOW WHO DON'T HAVE GOOD
PIECES WRITTEN ABOUT THEM,
BECAUSE WE DESERVE IT.
I HAVE WRITTEN ABOUT JIMI
HENDRIX, ELECTRIC LADY STUDIOS,
TONI MORRISON, KENDRICK LAMAR,
THE WATTS RIOTS, TRAYVON MARTIN,
RACHEL JEANTEL, DAVE CHAPPELLE.
WE DON'T ALWAYS HEAR ABOUT THE
PEOPLE WHO WE KNOW AS LEGENDS
THE WAYS THAT THEY WERE VERY
TRUE TO THEMSELVES.
I'M MORE INTERESTED IN THE
MOMENTS WHEN THEY WERE
UNCOMPROMISING AND THEY WERE
FEARLESS, BECAUSE WHAT I HOPE IS
THAT THAT FEARLESSNESS TELLS US
A LITTLE BIT ABOUT HOW WE CAN BE
FEARLESS.
WHAT WAS INTERESTING TO ME ABOUT
DAVE CHAPPELLE IS, HERE IS A
MOMENT WHERE TYPICALLY WALKING
AWAY FROM COMEDY CENTRAL,
WALKING AWAY FROM YOUR CAREER
WOULD BE A BAD DECISION, AND
ANYONE WOULD TELL YOU, DON'T DO
THAT.
THE COMMON UNDERSTANDING OF IT
IS, IS THAT HE FELT THAT THE
SHOW HAD STARTED TO CROSS A
LINE, AND THAT IT WAS ACTUALLY
BECOMING A SOURCE OF
EMBARRASSMENT.
AND SO WALKING AWAY FROM $50
MILLION WAS PRETTY HEROIC AND
PRETTY DECENT AND FULL OF
INTEGRITY.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I COULDN'T READ
UNTIL I WAS 12.
AND MAYBE I WASN'T 12, BUT I WAS
OLDER.
I THINK PEOPLE START READING
WHEN THEY'RE FIVE OR SOMETHING.
AND SO BOOKS WERE KIND OF THIS
PHANTASMAGORICAL SPACE THAT I
COULDN'T ENTER BECAUSE MY MOM
COULD READ.
MY DAD WAS AN ACADEMIC.
EVERYONE WAS SO INTELLIGENT.
AND I COULDN'T GO THERE.
AND THE MOMENT I COULD, I JUST
STARTED TO READ RAVENOUSLY.
ONE OF THE BOOKS THAT I REMEMBER
CHANGING EVERYONE'S LIVES WAS
"BELOVED."
THAT WAS THE FIRST TIME PEOPLE
WHO HAD BEEN SILENCED, ENSLAVED
PEOPLE, BECAME HUMAN.
AND, AT THAT MOMENT, I SAID,
THIS IS WHAT A WRITER CAN DO.
AND, SO, FOR ME, TONI MORRISON
DOESN'T EXIST ON A HUMAN PLANE.
SHE ALMOST EXISTS IN THIS ODD,
SPIRITUAL, OTHERWORLD, IN TERMS
OF HER WORK.
AND WHEN SHE WON THAT NOBEL
PRIZE, WHAT WAS INTERESTING IS
THAT A LOT OF PROMINENT
NEWSPAPERS ASKED, DOES THIS
WOMAN DESERVE IT?
SO, WHEN I HAD THE MOMENT TO
TAKE THE "NEW YORK TIMES"
MAGAZINE COVER, I DECIDED I'M
GOING TO TAKE THAT COVER TO LAY
FLOWERS AT THE FEET OF THIS
WOMAN AND SAY, NOT ONLY DID YOU
DESERVE IT, BUT THANK YOU.
MY NAME IS RACHEL KAADZI
GHANSAH, AND THIS IS MY BRIEF
BUT SPECTACULAR TAKE ON
FEARLESSNESS AND BLACK ART.
>> Woodruff: YOU CAN CATCH UP ON
OTHER BRIEF BUT SPECTACULAR
EPISODES ON OUR WEBSITE AT
pbs.org/newshour/brief.
JOIN US TONIGHT AT 9:00 P.M.
EASTERN FOR SPECIAL COVERAGE OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S STATE OF THE
UNION ADDRESS AND THE DEMOCRATIC
RESPONSE.
WE WILL CARRY BOTH SPEECHES LIVE
ON-AIR AND ONLINE AT
pbs.org/newshour, ALONG WITH
ANALYSIS AND FACT-CHECKING.
PLUS, YOU'LL WANT TO LISTEN TO A
SPECIAL STATE OF THE UNION
EPISODE OF OUR PODCAST, WITH THE
KIND OF SMART INSIGHTS AND
CONVERSATION YOU WON'T GET
ANYWHERE ELSE.
LOOK OUT FOR THE EPISODE IN OUR
PODCAST FEEDS, OR LISTEN ON OUR
WEBSITE WHEN IT'S RELEASED
pbs.org/newshour/podcasts.
AND THAT'S THE NEWSHOUR FOR NOW.
I'M JUDY WOODRUFF.
FOR ALL OF US AT THE PBS
NEWSHOUR, THANK YOU AND SEE YOU
SOON.
>> MAJOR FUNDING FOR THE PBS
NEWSHOUR HAS BEEN PROVIDED BY:
>> BABBEL.
A LANGUAGE APP THAT TEACHES
REAL-LIFE CONVERSATIONS IN A NEW
LANGUAGE.
>> AMERICAN CRUISE LINES.
>> THE FORD FOUNDATION.
WORKING WITH VISIONARIES ON THE
FRONTLINES OF SOCIAL CHANGE
WORLDWIDE.
>> CARNEGIE CORPORATION OF NEW
YORK.
SUPPORTING INNOVATIONS IN
EDUCATION, DEMOCRATIC
ENGAGEMENT, AND THE ADVANCEMENT
OF INTERNATIONAL PEACE AND
SECURITY.
AT carnegie.org.
>> AND WITH THE ONGOING SUPPORT
OF THESE INSTITUTIONS
AND INDIVIDUALS.
>> THIS PROGRAM WAS MADE
POSSIBLE BY THE CORPORATION FOR
PUBLIC BROADCASTING.
AND BY CONTRIBUTIONS TO YOUR PBS
STATION FROM VIEWERS LIKE YOU.
THANK YOU.
Captioning sponsored by
NEWSHOUR PRODUCTIONS, LLC
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
GATES: I'M HENRY
LOUIS GATES, JR.
WELCOME TO
FINDING YOUR ROOTS.