♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> TODAY, ON "RACHAEL RAY"!
GIADA IS SHOWING OFTEN CHOCOLATE
CAKE THAT IS HARD TO EXIST.
BUT DON'T TAKE OUR WORD FOR IT.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> IS DIRTY THAT BAD?
DO I HAVE TO BUY ORGANIC MEAT?
SHOULD I BE COUNTED CALORIES?
>> YOU'VE GOT QUESTIONS, WE'VE
GOT ANSWERS.
>> DITCH THE CALCULATORS, WE
DON'T NEED TO BE COUNTING OUR
CALORIES!
>> PLUS, LOOK WHO BETH STERN
BROUGHT WITH HER!
YOU GOT TO BE KITTEN ME!
AND RACHAEL IS CATCHING UP WITH
THE GOOD OLD FRIEND OVER DINNER.
>> THERE YOU GO, KIDS!
SPAGHETTI AND MEATBALLS!
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: WELCOME,
EVERYBODY!
EVERYBODY KNOWS MY FIRST GUEST
FROM FOOD NETWORK, OF COURSE,
AND NOW SHE IS SERVING UP
CHALLENGES TO SOME OF THE
COUNTRY'S TOP BAKERS ON A NEW
SHOW CALLED "WINTER CAKE ALL."
CHECK HER OUT.
>> TONIGHT, MY FRIEND, GUY
FIERI.
>> WE ARE GETTING READY TO
CELEBRATE OUR 250TH EPISODE, AND
I WANT TO THANK THE CAST AND
CREW.
I WANT THE CAKE TO BE
OUT-OF-BOUNDS!
SPEAK OF THE BAKERS WILL SERVE
UP SOME SWEET SUCCESSES.
>> WE WILL JUST PILE IT HIGH.
>> OH, WOW.
>> I LOVE A CAKE THAT DEMANDS I
WALK AROUND IT.
>> AND SOME CAKE-TASTROPHES.
>> THAT'S A CAKE?
>> FIND OUT WHO WILL TASTE
VICTORY, ON "WINNER CAKE ALL."
>> Rachael: PLEASE WELCOME,
GIADA de LAURENTIIS!
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
SOME OF THOSE CAKES WERE AWESOME
AND SOME OF THEM --
CAKE-TASTROPHE.
YOU SAID IN THE PROMO HAVE YOU
HAD BEFORE?
I TRIED TO MAKE A CAKE FOR MY
MOM AT HER BIRTHDAY.
I'M DIVORCED, BUT WHEN I GOT
MARRIED, I LOVE THE IDEA OF
TOPSY-TURVY CAKE SO I GOT ONE OF
THOSE.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE REALLY
COOL.
BEFORE WE SET DOWN FOR DINNER.
THANK GOODNESS I HAD ALREADY
DONE MY VOWS.
BUT I WAS IN TEARS.
I REMEMBER, MY MOM WAS LIKE, "NO
ONE WILL REMEMBER, IT WILL JUST
BE A GREAT STORY."
AND I TOLD THAT STORY FOR YEARS
AND YEARS.
CAKE-TASTROPHES CAN BE GOOD.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: THIS IS A CAKE
WITH A LOT OF APPEAL.
TELL THEM WHAT YOU WILL BE
MAKING TODAY.
>> Giada: I'M MAKING A CLASSIC
ITALIAN CAKE FROM THE ISLAND OF
CAPRI.
IT'S CALLED TORTA CAPRESE.
IT'S BASICALLY A FLOURLESS
CHOCOLATE CAKE.
IT'S GOT ALMOND FLOUR, IT'S A
GLUTEN-FREE CHOCOLATE CAKE IS
WHAT I SHOULD HAVE SAID.
IT'S DEFINITELY NOT
"STAR WARSY," BUT IT'S
DELICIOUS.
>> Rachael: IT'S NOT A
COMPLICATED, GIANT PROJECT.
>> Giada: IT'S LIKE A
GRANDMA'S CAKE.
>> Rachael: YOU HAVE A CUP OF
COFFEE, YOU TALK, IT'S THAT KIND
OF CAKE.
>> Giada: MY FAVORITE KIND OF
CAKE.
>> Rachael: MINE, TOO.
WHAT YOU WANT ME TO DO?
>> Giada: WE NEED TO SEPARATE
EGGS.
I REALLY DON'T LIKE SEPARATE
>> Rachael: I BAKE AT ALL.
EGGS.
>> Giada: WE WILL MAKE SURE
>> Rachael: I BAKE AT ALL.
SHELL DOESN'T GET IN THERE.
>> Giada: WE WILL MAKE SURE
>> Rachael: IF YOU GET SHELL
SHELL DOESN'T GET IN THERE.
IN THERE, SHELL-LIKE SHELL.
>> Rachael: IF YOU GET SHELL
IT WILL BE ATTRACTED TO THE BIG
IN THERE, SHELL-LIKE SHELL.
PIECE OF SHELL.
IT WILL BE ATTRACTED TO THE BIG
>> Giada: WE HAVE ONE HAND
PIECE OF SHELL.
MIXER SO I GUESS WE HAVE TO BEAT
>> Giada: WE HAVE ONE HAND
BOTH OF THESE GUYS.
MIXER SO I GUESS WE HAVE TO BEAT
>> Rachael: PRETTY GOOD, NOT
BOTH OF THESE GUYS.
BAD!
>> Rachael: PRETTY GOOD, NOT
[APPLAUSE]
BAD!
TELL EVERYBODY ABOUT THE PREMISE
[APPLAUSE]
OF THE SHOW.
TELL EVERYBODY ABOUT THE PREMISE
WHERE'D YOU GET THE CONTESTANTS?
OF THE SHOW.
>> THE CONTESTANTS ARE FROM ALL
WHERE'D YOU GET THE CONTESTANTS?
OF THE COUNTRY.
>> THE CONTESTANTS ARE FROM ALL
THEY ARE ALL PROFESSONAL
OF THE COUNTRY.
BAKERS.
THEY ARE ALL PROFESSONAL
THEY HAVE BIG, BIG SHOPS, THEY
BAKERS.
DO THIS FOR A LIVING.
THEY HAVE BIG, BIG SHOPS, THEY
SO THAT'S FANTASTIC.
DO THIS FOR A LIVING.
THEY HAVE TO GO THROUGH TWO
SO THAT'S FANTASTIC.
ROUNDS.
THEY HAVE TO GO THROUGH TWO
AND THE SECOND ROUND IS WHEN
ROUNDS.
THEY GET TO MEET THE CLIENT.
AND THE SECOND ROUND IS WHEN
THE CLIENT IS THE PERSON THEY
THEY GET TO MEET THE CLIENT.
ARE BREAKING THE CAKE FOR, AND
THE CLIENT IS THE PERSON THEY
THE CLIENT IS ALSO THE ONE WHO'S
ARE BREAKING THE CAKE FOR, AND
GOING TO PICK THE CAKE.
THE CLIENT IS ALSO THE ONE WHO'S
SO ALTHOUGH WE HAVE ALL THESE
GOING TO PICK THE CAKE.
JUDGES, PROFESSIONAL BAKING
SO ALTHOUGH WE HAVE ALL THESE
PEOPLE WHO JUDGE, REALLY IS UP
JUDGES, PROFESSIONAL BAKING
TO THE CLIENT TO DECIDE.
PEOPLE WHO JUDGE, REALLY IS UP
A LOT OF PEOPLE PIG LOOKS OVER
TO THE CLIENT TO DECIDE.
TASTE.
A LOT OF PEOPLE PIG LOOKS OVER
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
TASTE.
>> Rachael: EXACTLY, IT
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
DEPENDS.
>> Rachael: EXACTLY, IT
>> Giada: I MUST SAY, WE HAD
DEPENDS.
GUYS -- WHICH WAS INTERESTING,
>> Giada: I MUST SAY, WE HAD
TO SEE IT ALL AND THESE CAKES.
GUYS -- WHICH WAS INTERESTING,
>> Rachael:
WE HAVE ONE WITH QUINTUPLE
LITTLE GIRLS.
THEY ARE FOUR, I THINK.
OH, MY GOODNESS -- ONE OF THE
MADE FELL OFF.
THEY DIDN'T EVEN NOTICE.
IT WAS SO EXTRAORDINARY.
THESE ARE EXTRAORDINARY PIECES
OF ART.
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND,
TEMPERATURES FLUCTUATE.
WE'RE SHOOTING OUTSIDE.
>> Rachael: OH, MAN!
FORGET ABOUT IT.
>> Giada: SO IT'S HOT AND
COLD -- >> Rachael: SO IT'S
NOT THE CAKE'S FRIENDS.
>> Giada: SO THE CAKES GO,
"WOMP, WOMP, WOMP."
LET'S DO THIS ONE FIRST.
WE WILL ADD A CUP OF SUGAR.
I'VE GOT TWO STICKS OF BUTTER
AND ONE HALF CUPS OF
DARK CHOCOLATE THAT I MELTED
OVER A DOUBLE BOILER, WHICH I'VE
GOT TO SAY, MY FAVORITE THING
WHEN I DO THIS IS TO DO THAT DO
THAT.
>> Rachael: JUST TO MAKE SURE.
OH, LOOK!
THERE'S ANOTHER CAKE!
>> Giada: LIFESAVER.
A PINCH OF SALT, JUST A FLAVOR
THE CAKE AND TO STABILIZE THE
EGG WHITES A BIT.
I'M DONE WITH THIS.
THERE WE GO.
SO YOU WANT TO DO THE YOLKS, AS
YOU KNOW, UNTIL THEY ARE PALE.
>> Rachael: WHIPPED CREAM?
>> Giada: DON'T PUT THAT IN
THERE.
THEN --
YOU WANT TO SPLIT?
JUST SO PEOPLE CAN SEE WHAT IT
LOOKS LIKE WHEN YOU'RE DONE WITH
THE EGG WHITES.
>> Rachael: IT SO LOUD, YOU
CAN'T HEAR!
>> Giada: I KNOW, I KNOW.
WE'VE GOT TO BAKE, RIGHT!
I'VE GOT TO BAKE SOMETHING!
[APPLAUSE]
I ADDED THE MELTED CHOCOLATE AND
BUTTER TO THE EGGS.
>> Rachael: DOES JADE LIKE TO
GET INTO THE KITCHEN?
DOES SHE LIKE TO BAKE?
HOW OLD IS SHE NOW?
>> Giada: SHE DOES STILL LIKE
TO BAKE, SHE'S TEN.
>> Rachael: SHE LOOKS LIKE A
YOUNG LADY NOW!
SHE DOESN'T LOOK LIKE A LITTLE
GIRL!
>> Giada: SHE IS TEN AND SHE
LOVES TO BAKE.
SHE DOES MADE BROWNIES THE OTHER
DAY.
I THINK IT'S BECAUSE THEY WANT
TO STICK THEIR FINGERS IN.
SAVORY FOOD, NOT SO MUCH.
ALMOST FLOUR, ONE AND A HALF
CUPS.
>> Rachael: A LITTLE VANILLA.
>> Giada: THERE WE GO.
THE REASON IT'S ALMOND FLOUR IS
BECAUSE IN CAPRI THEY HAVE A LOT
OF ALMONDS.
SO THEY USE ALMOND FLOUR TO MAKE
A LOT OF THEIR CAKES.
>> Rachael: PUT THESE GUYS IN?
>> Giada: YEAH, GO.
>> Rachael: I DON'T HAVE --
>> Giada: I WILL DO IT.
IT DOESN'T KEEP IT AS LIGHT
OTHERWISE.
THEN YOU POOR THIS BATTER INTO
YOUR SPRING FORM PAN THAT YOU
GUYS LINED NICELY, AND BUTTERED.
>> Rachael: A LITTLE BIT OF
PARCHMENT ON THE BOTTOM.
A LITTLE BUTTER.
>> Giada: IT MAKES IT EASIER.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO DO THE PARCHMENT.
YOU CAN JUST LEAVE IT ON THE
BASE UNTIL YOU GET THE POINT
WHERE YOU SLIP IT OUT.
BUT IS MORE PROFESSIONAL IF YOU
DO THAT.
YOU PUT IN THERE, 350 FOR
40 MINUTES.
THEN HE CAN DO THE REST.
THE REASON YOU WANT TO DO
HALF-AND-HALF --
[APPLAUSE]
IT KEEPS IT LIGHT.
OTHERWISE YOU KILL IT.
>> Rachael: WE'VE GOT ONE DOWN
HERE.
>> Giada: WANT TO TASTE IT?
HAVE YOU EVER HAD A TORTA
CAPRESE?
IN THE SOUTH OF ITALY THEY MAKE
IT EVERYWHERE.
>> Rachael: I HAVE COME ON MY
MOM IS SICILIAN, ACTUALLY.
>> Giada: SO YOU GUYS MAKE IT,
TOO!
>> Rachael: WE LIKE OLIVE OIL
CAKES, CAKES THAT ARE NOT TOO
DENSE OR SWEET OR COMPLICATED
WITH A TON OF FROSTING.
>> Giada: YEAH, WE ARE NOT
TRUSTING PEOPLE IN ITALY.
BUT WISH IT WAS ALL ABOUT IT.
FUNDED, ALL THESE THINGS
THEY NEVER KNEW ANYTHING ABOUT.
>> Rachael: WHAT YOU CAN DO
WITH IT IS AMAZING CREATIVE
REALLY IS AN ART FORM.
>> Giada: THEY WOULD MAKE
GLASS BALLS FROM SUGAR.
IT WAS SO HOT, WHEN LADY BIRD
HER HAND REALLY BADLY.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
IT WAS A CRYSTAL BALL BECAUSE&
THEY WERE DOING BECAUSE THEY
WERE DOING A FORTUNE TELLER SORT
OF THING.
I LEARNED SO MUCH ON THAT SHOW.
SO MUCH.
[APPLAUSE]
SO MUCH THAT I KNOW I DON'T WANT
A BAKERY!
>> Rachael: OH, MY GOD, IT'S
SO GOOD!
>> Giada: MY TEA IS IN THE
SINK.
IS IT STILL THERE?
EXCELLENT!
>> Rachael: WE MADE A LITTLE
BIT OF TIME AT THE END OF THIS
SEGMENT SO WE COULD DO A LITTLE
BIT OF Q&A.
OR Q AND R AND Q AND G.
JOEY, THIS IS THE ONLY EXERCISE
DELEGATES.
TOP ROW, WE WANT SOMEONE FROM
THE UPPER DECK.
GIVE THE GUY A COUPLE EXTRA
STEPS TODAY.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> HI, RACHAEL.
MY NAME IS JILL.
>> Rachael: HI, JILL!
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE TO KNOW?
>> HOW ARE YOU?
MY QUESTION IS FOR YOU.
STARTING TO KICK MY KIDS WHEN
THEY WERE YOUNGER, AND NOW MY
GRANDDAUGHTER.
TIMES OF CHANGE.
ONE SUGGESTION OF AN AGE TO GET
THEM STARTED IN THE KITCHEN AND
LETTING THEM COOK ON THEIR OWN?
>> Rachael: MY MAMA ALWAYS HAD
US IN THE KITCHEN WITH HER.
FROM BIRTH.
ALWAYS ON HER HIP.
THOSE ARE MY SPHERE OF MEMORIES,
BEING
IN THE KITCHEN.
ON MY MOM'S HIP, AND WITH MY
GRANDPA WHEN HE WAS STILL WITH
US.
MY SISTER HAD A REALLY CUTE
THING WITH MY NIECE AND NEPHEW
WHEN THEY WERE LITTLE.
SHE WOULD GIVE THEM PLASTIC
CUTLERY, LIKE A PLASTIC KNIFE
AND PLASTIC TOOLS SO THEY COULD
MIMIC HER WITHOUT ACTUALLY
PLAYING WITH KNIVES WHEN THEY
WERE ONE TREND OR 2.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
AGREED?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Giada: I WAS CLEANING OUT
THE KNIFE SO THE CULINARY
DOESN'T HAVE TO CLEAN IT!
I SAY SINCE BIRTH.
I USED TO HAVE JADE IN A LITTLE
SWING WHILE I COOK.
SHE SAT THERE.
SHE WASHED ME, AND I THINK THE
SOONER YOU DO IT THE BETTER.
CHILDREN ARE SPONGES.
THEY SAY THAT FROM 0 TO 3 IS
WHEN THEY ABSORB THE MOST.
SO THE MORE THAT YOU GIVE THEM
AT THAT TIME, PEOPLE THINK, "OH,
NO, I WANT TO IN THE KITCHEN."
PUT THEM IN THAT LITTLE SWING
AND LEAVE THEM THERE.
THEY LOVE WATCHING YOU MOVE.
>> Rachael: AND THEY GET USED
TO THE AROMAS AND LEARN BY
OSMOSIS.
THEY SEE WHAT YOU WERE DOING.
MY MOM ALSO NEVER BOUGHT BABY
FOOD.
SHE WOULD JUST BLEND UP IN A
BLENDER WHATEVER SHE WAS MAKING,
COOKING, AND EATING.
SHE WOULDN'T GIVE US THE SPACE
EAST OF THINGS.
>> Gada: THAT'S WHAT MY MOM
DID, AND THAT'S WHAT I DID!
[APPLAUSE]
IT DEVELOPS THEIR PALATE.
>> Rachael: GO FOR IT!
JOE, YOU ARE STICKING TO THE
LOW!
OKAY, OKAY.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> HI, MY NAME IS LISA.
>> Rachael: HI, LISA!
>> I HAVE A KID QUESTION COME
ALSO.
I HAVE TWO GO GREAT KIDS, AND MY
DAUGHTER IS ABOUT TO BE A
TEENAGER.
I'M LOOKING FOR HEALTHY SNACKS I
CAN SEND WITH HER TO SCHOOL.
SHE'S THERE FOR A LONG DAY NOW,
SHE'S EATING MORE JUNK.
>> Giada: SNACKS, I HAVE TO
SAY, THE TOUGHEST.
AS A MOM, I COULD TELL YOU.
THEY HAVE A 10-YEAR-OLD.
THEY ARE THE TOUGHEST THING.
JADE ONLY WANTS BAGGED SNACKS.
>> Rachael: THEY WANT WITH ALL
THE ADVOCATES HAVE.
SPEAK TO HER FAVORITE RIGHT NOW
IS SALAMI AND CHEESE AND
CRACKERS.
THEY HAVE THOSE SNACK PACKS, I
TRY TO FIND SOMETHING THAT'S --
WELL, NO SULFATES, KNOW THIS,
KNOW THAT.
BUT SHE LOVES THOSE THINGS.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES HER FEEL COOL.
POPCORN.
SHE REALLY LIKES POPCORN.
I DO POPCORN FOR HER.
I MEAN, I HAVE POPCORN THAT I
ALSO DO MYSELF.
I'D DO POPCORN, I DO THAT, I TRY
TO CUT UP VEGETABLES WITH
RANCH --
>> Rachael: AND DIP IN THE
BOTTOM, YEAH.
>> Giada: I WILL BE HONEST,
HALF THE TIME SHE DOESN'T EAT
IT.
>> Rachael: THEY CAN'T EVEN
TRADE THEM AWAY BECAUSE NOBODY
WANTS IT!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Giada: I THINK SUSHI, SHE
FISH.
VEGETABLE SUSHI, MORE LIKE
AVOCADO, CUCUMBER.
BECAUSE FISH DOESN'T SIT WELL.
STUFF LIKE THAT, SHE REALLY
ENJOYS.
HOMEMADE TRAIL MIX IS.
I PUT LOTS OF CHOCOLATE CHIPS IN
THERE SO IT MAKES IT MORE FUN.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: TRAIL MIX IS A
GOOD ONE.
YOU CAN USE LOTS OF THINGS THEY
LIKE.
>> Giada: PUMPKIN CAN BE IN
THERE
, CHOCOLATE.
>> HI IT, I'M JOSEPHINE.
I JUST WANT TO NO, WHEN YOU ARE
AT HOME RELAXING ABOUT WHAT IS
YOUR EASY GO-TO MEAL THAT YOU
MAKE?
>> Giada: I LIKE SOUPS AND
SALADS.
>> Rachael: ILIFE SUIT BECAUSE
IT CAN LAST FOR SEVERAL DAYS.
I LOVE EGGS.
I LOVE SCRAMBLED EGGS.
OR A FRITTATA OR SOMETHING.
EGGS ARE EASY.
>> Giada: WE USED TO EAT EGGS
FOR DINNER.
IN ITALY YOU EAT THEM FOR
DINNER, NOT BREAKFAST.
IN ITALY, GROWING UP, I NEVER
HAD EGGS FOR BREAKFAST.
WE JUST DON'T DO THAT.
BUT WE HAD EGGS FOR DINNER ALL
THE TIME.
>> SOUNDS GOOD, THANK YOU.
>> Rachael: THOSE ARE GOOD
GO-TOES.
THANK YOU TO GIADA, UP NEXT IS
KERI GLASSMAN!
SHE WILL ANSWER HER MOST
FREQUENTLY ASKED QUESTIONS,
RIGHT AFTER THIS!
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> TOMORROW -- >> WE ARE GOING
TO WIN THIS!
>> CLEAR THE WAY!
>> WE ARE COMING FOR YOU.
>> OUR 12TH ANNUAL SUPER BOWL
RECIPE PLAYOFF IS A FAMILY
AFFAIR!
>> SMELL THAT VICTORY!
>> AND CHEF RICHARD BLAIS AND
HIS DISCERNING DAUGHTERS DECIDE
WHICH OF THESE NFL FAMILIES IS
GOING TO SCORE!
>> THE WINNER IS...
>> PLUS, DON'T FUMBLE YOUR
SUPER BOWL PARTY!
WE'VE GOT SOME SMASHING DECOR
IDEAS!
A SMOKING SUPER BOWL APPETIZER.
>> THREE, TWO, ONE, THERE IT IS!
>> OH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> AND RACH IS GOING DEEP!
>> THEY ARE GORGEOUS.
>> WITH A SMOKY CHORIZO BLITZ
BURGER.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> OUR 12TH ANNUAL SUPER BOWL
RECIPE
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: ALL RIGHT!
WILL COME BACK FROM EVERYBODY.
WE ARE JOINED NOW BY ONE OF OUR
FAVORITES.
SHE IS A DIETITIAN AND A FOUNDER
OF NUTRITIOUS LIFE, HER LOVELY
FRIEND, KERI GLASSMAN!
SHE'S HERE TODAY TO GO THROUGH
SOME OF HER MOST ASKED
QUESTIONS, BECAUSE THERE IS A
TON OF CONFLICTING INFORMATION
OUT THERE WHEN IT COMES TO
NUTRITION.
PEOPLE WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S WHAT
BEFORE THEY GO SHOPPING AND MAKE
GOOD CHOICES.
SO, KERI -- OUR HOUSE AND OUR
PRODUCE IS YOURS.
TAKE IT AWAY.
WHERE DO WE START?
>> Keri: THIS IS ONE OF MY
FAVORITE THINGS, FIRST OF ALL.
ANSWERING NUTRITION QUESTIONS.
I'M SO EXCITED ABOUT TODAY.
FIRST, I'M GOING TO GRAB MY
GROCERY CARD.
ONE QUESTION I GET ALL THE TIME,
IS ICEBERG LETTUCE REALLY WORTH
IT?
DOES IT HAVE ANY NUTRITIONAL
VALUE?
THE ANSWER IS, IT DOES.
FIRST OF ALL, IT'S FILLED WITH
WATER VOLUME SO HELPS FILL YOU
UP.
AS VITAMINS E AND C.
IT IS GIVING IT A LITTLE BIT OF
NUTRIENTS.
OF COURSE, I WOULD PREFER THAT
YOU HAVE DARKER GREEN LEAFY
VEGETABLES LIKE KALE.
I LOVE MY KALE, AND OTHER DARK
GREENS.
>> Rachael: BUT IF YOU'RE
MAKING A BURGER OR IT'S TACO
NIGHT, A LITTLE BIT OF LETTUCE
IS NOT GOING TO HURT YOU.
>> Keri: THE OTHER THING IS,
IT'S A GOOD VEHICLE.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE DARK GREENS,
IT'S A GOOD VEHICLE FOR OTHER
VEGETABLES SUCH AS CARROTS AND
SPINACH.
WE MET NOT LIKE THE DARK GREENS,
BUT THEY ARE HERE ANYWAY.
ONIONS, TOMATOES, PEPPERS.
IT'S A GREAT VEHICLE.
JUST DON'T LOAD IT UP AT THE
RANCH DRESSING AND THE BACON.
USE IT TO GET IN SOME OTHER
NUTRIENTS!
[LAUGHTER]
DON'T SKIP IT.
>> Rachael: A CUP OF BLEU
CHEESE DRESSING WITH MAYONNAISE,
SOUR CREAM, CHEESE.
YOU PUT ON LIKE THIS MUCH
LETTUCE.
>> Keri: USE IT FOR GOOD!
GET IN SOME OTHER NUTRIENTS IN
THERE.
DON'T PASS ON THE SALAD.
THE OTHER QUESTION IS, DO HAVE
TO STOP EATING BY A CERTAIN TIME
AT NIGHT?
WHAT I USUALLY TELL PEOPLE IS
IT'S NOT ABOUT THE TIME AT
NIGHT.
IT'S REALLY ABOUT YOUR SCHEDULE.
IF YOU GET UP AND HAVE BREAKFAST
AT 6, YOUR DINNER MIGHT BE AT 7.
BUT IF YOU HAVE BREAKFAST AT 10,
YOUR DINNER MIGHT BE AT 9.
THAT'S PERFECTLY FINE.
THE PROBLEM IS THAT PEOPLE,
USUALLY WHEN THEY EAT LATE AT
NIGHT THEY ARE EATING EXTRA
CALORIES AND THEY ARE EATING
EMOTIONAL CALORIES OF FOODS LIKE
CHIPS AND THOSE COOKIES THAT
YOUR KIDS MADE.
THE LEFT OVERS.
THEY CAN OFTEN NOT ONLY ADD ON
EXTRA UNHEALTHY CALORIES, BUT
DISRUPT YOUR SLEEP.
SO IF YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE
SOMETHING AT NIGHT AND YOU ARE
TRULY HUNGRY, HAVE SOMETHING
THAT'S GOING TO WORK FOR YOU A
LITTLE BIT.
BUT ANNA, FOR EXAMPLE, WITH A
LITTLE BIT OF ALMOND BUTTER.
IT'S A GREAT TREAT.
BUT IN HIS HAVE MAGNESIUM, WHICH
IS COMMON, THEY CAN HELP
INCREASE THE PRODUCTION OF
MELATONIN.
THE NATURAL HORMONE FOR SLEEP.
ALSO, A LITTLE BIT OF TART
CHERRY JUICE ACTUALLY COULD DO
SOME WONDERS.
IT'S BEEN RESEARCHED AND THERE
HAS BEEN -- IT'S BEEN SHOWN THAT
IT CAN HELP IMPROVE YOUR SLEEP.
>> Rachael: WHAT ABOUT WINE
BECAUSE DIMMICK MIKE [LAUGHTER]
THAT PUTS ME RIGHT TO SLEEP
!
I HAVE CHERRIES IN MY CHEEKS!
>> ANOTHER QUESTION I GET, IS
DAIRY THAT BAD?
YOU KNOW WHAT, IT IS NOT!
I'M A FAN OF DAIRY.
A LITTLE BIT OF CHEESE TO GO A
LONG WAY AS FAR AS SATISFACTION
GOES.
WE KNOW THAT DAIRY HAS CALCIUM
AND PROTEIN, AND EVEN WHOLE FAT
DAIRY -- WHICH I'M ACTUALLY A
BIGGER FAN OF -- HAS A SATURATED
FAT IN IT BUT IT DOES HAVE SOME
HEALTH BENEFITS.
ALL SATURATED FAT IS NOT
NECESSARILY BAD FOR YOU.
THE NEXT THING PEOPLE ASK ME --
>> Rachael: I MEAN, THERE ARE
PEOPLE THAT HAVE AN ALLERGY TO
DAIRY.
THAT, I UNDERSTAND.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE AN ALLERGY, IT
KIND OF AN "ALL THINGS IN
MODERATION" SORT OF A THING?
>> Keri: I'M GLAD YOU BROUGHT
THAT UP, BECAUSE I WAS GOOD TO
START BY SAYING -- IF YOU DON'T
HAVE A LACTOSE INTOLERANCE OR
ANALOGY, OR YOU'RE NOT A VEGAN,
THEN IT CAN ABSOLUTELY HAVE A
PLACE IN YOUR DIET.
>> Rachael: HEALTH BENEFITS.
>> Keri: YOU DO WANT TO HAVE
IT IN MODERATION.
YOU MIGHT NOT WANT TO HAVE A
BREAKFAST LUNCH AND DINNER, BUT
THERE'S A PLACE IN YOUR DIET FOR
IT.
ESPECIALLY THE BIG, HEALTHY,
WHOLE FOOD DIET.
THE NEXT QUESTION I GET IS ABOUT
MEATS.
DO I HAVE TO BUY ORGANIC MEAT?
WHAT I LIKE TO TELL PEOPLE IS,
IF YOU COULD BUY ALL ORGANIC,
THAT'S GREAT.
BUT IT'S EXPENSIVE.
IF YOU HAVE TO PICK AND
CHOOSE -- WHICH MOST OF US DO --
I WOULD SAY TO PUT SOME OF THE
GROCERY BILL TOWARD ORGANIC
MEAT.
THINK ABOUT IT.
WITH PRODUCE, OU CAN WASH AWAY
SOME OF THOSE PESTICIDES.
WHEN IT COMES TO ME, YOU'LL BE
ABLE TO WASH AWAY THE HORMONES
AND THE ANTIBIOTICS.
>> Rachael: IT'S ALSO VERY
MUCH ABOUT HOW THE ANIMALS ARE
TREATED AND FARMED TO BEGIN
WITH.
>> Keri: ABSOLUTELY.
>> Rachael: I WOULD RATHER SEE
PEOPLE EAT LESS MEAT OF BETTER
QUALITY THAN EAT 100% --
IS BETTER FOR THEM AND FOR THE
ANIMALS.
>> Keri: BLOCK OFF THE MEAT
AND HAVE A BEAN DISH ONE DAY.
A BLACK BEAN SOUP.
I'M A FAN OF ALL NUT BUTTERS.
PITA BUTTER AND ALMOND BUTTER.
PEOPLE ALWAYS ASK ME, WHAT
SHOULD I HAVE?
>> Rachael: CAN YOU HAVE BOTH?
>> Keri: YES, YOU CAN!
I HAVE BOTH AT BONE.
ALMOND BUTTER MAYBE HAS MORE
CALCIUM, BUT THEY ARE BOTH
HEALTHY CHOICES.
THE ONE THING YOU HAVE TO MAKE
SURE OF IS THAT YOU ALWAYS GO
NATURAL.
ALMOND BUTTER IS GENERALLY
EASIER TO FIND NATURAL.
PEANUT BUTTER, YOU HAVE TO MAKE
SURE YOU READ THE LABEL AND
INGREDIENTS.
IT SAYS "INGREDIENTS,
PEANUT BUTTER."
MANY OF THEM HAVE ADDED SUGAR.
>> Rachael: CORN TRIPS.
RIGHT.
>> Keri: JUST LIKE YOU SHOULD
HAVE MULTIPLE VEGETABLES, HAVE
MULTIPLE TYPES OF NUT BUTTER I
YOUR HOUSE.
[APPLAUSE]
THE LAST QUESTION I GET, SHOULD
I BE COUNTING CALORIES?
I SAY DITCH THE CALCULATORS!
YOU DON'T NEED TO BE COUNTING
CALORIES!
>> Rachael: IT IS SO UPTIGHT.
THAT'S WHY I WRITE FREEHAND
EQUIVALENTS.
I DON'T WANT PEOPLE IN THE
KITCHEN MEASURING A TEASPOON OF
THIS, A TEASPOON OF THAT.
NO!
IT'S A DRAG, MAN!
>> Keri: EAT THE HOLE, REAL
FOODS.
LISTEN TO YOUR BODY.
STOP WHEN YOU ARE SATISFIED.
CALORIES AREN'T CREATED EQUAL.
100 CALORIES OF JELLY BEAN IS AT
THE SAME AS 100 CALORIES OF A
LITTLE APPLE AND PEANUT BUTTER.
THAT HAS LOTS OF NUTRIENTS AND
WILL SATISFY YOU.
>> Rachael: THAT'S MY GIRL!
[APPLAUSE]
SO MANY GREAT, TALENTED WOMEN IN
THIS SHOW!
UP NEXT GO UNDER THE GRIFFIN
DIVIDE.
MY DEAR FRIEND, BETH STERN.
SHE IS HERE WITH SOME FURRY
FRIENDS FIRST.
IT'S ALMOST TIME FOR
KITTEN BOWL!
AFTER THIS.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> IT IS THE ONE, THE ONLY, BETH
STERN.
TAKE IT AWAY, BETH.
>> THINK YOU GUYS.
I'M SO HAPPY TO BE JOINING YOU!
ONCE AGAIN, FOR KITTEN BOWL 6.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS OUR SIX
SEASON.
THIS YEAR, KITTEN BOWL SIX IS
BIGGER AND BETTER THAN EVER.
IN ADDITION TO THE MOST INTIMATE
FOOTBALL IN OUR HISTORY, WE HAVE
THE PRIVILEGE OF SHARING STORIES
OF RESCUE AND ADOPTION WE GET IT
INSIDE LOOK ON THE INSPIRING
STORIES ABOUT HOW THE SKINS MADE
HERE TONIGHT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: HONESTLY, KITTENS
AND PUPPIES.
CAN HE START THE DAY ANY BETTER?
QUESTION MARCUS IS ONE OF MY
FAVORITE PEOPLE IN THE PLANT.
BETH STERN IS BACK WITH US
TODAY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Beth: THANK YOU!
>> Rachael: OF COURSE, THAT
ACTION-PACKED FOOTAGE WAS A CLIP
FROM KITTEN BOWL.
SHE'S HOSTING AND, OF COURSE.
CAN WE TALK ABOUT THE KITTENS IN
OUR LAPS CLOSE TO MARK THEY ARE
THE CUTEST!
>> Beth: IF ANYBODY HAS GOT
OUTSIDE, WOULD YOU ALL HAVE COME
IT'S FREEZING IN NEW YORK CITY.
THESE KITTENS WERE FOUND OUTSIDE
A WEEK AGO.
NORTH SHORE ANIMAL LEAGUE
AMERICA RESCUED THEM AND BROUGHT
THEM TO SAFELY COME INTO OUR
SHELTER IN FORT WASHINGTON.
THEY ARE VACCINATED, HEALTHY,
AND READY FOR ADOPTION NOW.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: BEAUTIFUL!
>> Beth: RACHAEL IS HOLDING A
LITTLE BOY NAMED BUBBA BOOEY.
AND WE HAVE THESE TWO, JOHNNY.
>> Rachael: THEY WERE
ABANDONED IN THE COLD!
BETH AND HOWARD, THEY LITERALLY
RESCUE CAPS OFF THE STREET.
I REMEMBER A STORY -- YOU WERE
IN FLORIDA AND BETH LITERALLY
TOOK THE SHIRT OFF HER BACK TO
RESCUE A CAT FOR A CLIMB THROUGH
FENCE COME AND RESCUE A KITTEN.
YOU GUYS HAVE RESCUED ABOUT 900
CATS?
>> Beth: CLOSE TO 900, YES.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: NORTH SHORE ANIMAL
LEAGUE AMERICA WHICH THEY WORK
WITH AND CHAMPION, I THINK THEY
ARE THE GREATEST PEOPLE ON THE
FRONT LINES OF EVERY BIG RESCUE
AFTER EVERY MAJOR DISASTER.
I WANT TO GIVE A PLUG TO OUR
FOOD, NUTRISH.
BECAUSE OF THAT FOOD WE HAVE
GIVEN OVER $30 MILLION IN
RESCUE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
OUR PARTNERS ARE NORTH SHORE
ANIMAL LEAGUE AMERICA.
>> Beth: YOU ARE HERE TO US
AND OUR MISSION.
>> Rachael: WHAT YOU DO SO IS
SO IMPORTANT!
900 KIDDIES.
YOU WILL BE UP TO FOUR DIGIT
SOON.
>> Beth: LET ME MAKE THIS
CLEAR, IT'S 900 -- NOT ALL AT
ONCE.
>> Rachael: THEY FOSTER THEM,
RIGHT?
DIDN'T YOU TELL ME THAT YOU AND
HOWARD, FOR HIS BIRTHDAY COME
YOU JUST KIND OF SNUGGLED UP
WITH THE KITTENS?
>> Beth: HE AND I USUALLY GO
TO BED AT 8:00.
I THINK WE STAYED UP UNTIL 8:30.
OUR IDEAL NIGHT, WHICH YOU KNOW,
IS AT HOME WITH A GLASS OF WINE
AND ALL OF OUR CATS AROUND US.
THE KITTIES.
[APPLAUSE]
IT'S SO SAD!
BECAUSE IT'S NOT KITTEN SEASON,
IT'S SO RARE WE HAVE THESE
KITTENS IN THE SHELTER.
BUT A LOT OF PEOPLE DON'T MAKE
PLANS FOR THEIR ANIMALS IF
SOMETHING HAPPENS TO THEM.
SO RIGHT NOW I'M GETTING CALLS.
SO MANY SENIOR CATS WHOSE OWNERS
HAVE PASSED AWAY.
I HAVE THREE RIGHT NOW IN OUR
HOUSE.
THEY ARE 15, 16, AND 14-YEAR-OLD
CATS THAT HAVE BEEN INCREDIBLE
PETS AND LOVED THEIR ENTIRE
LIVES, AND THEY WOULD BE
INITIALED IF THEY WEREN'T IN OUR
HOME.
FOSTERING IS IMPORTANT.
I KNOW I'M GOING TO FIND THEM
INCREDIBLE HOMES, BUT THE POINT
IS, MAKE PLANS FOR YOUR PETS IF
SOMETHING WAS TO HAPPEN.
>> Rachael: JUST LIKE ANY
OTHER FAMILY MEMBER OF YOURS TO
ME SHOULD PROVIDE FOR THEM IF
CIRCUMSTANCES MEAN THAT YOU
CAN'T.
HI!
HI IT, SWEETIE!
YOU'RE SO HANDSOME!
>> Beth: IN ADDITION TO THE
KITTEN BOWL THIS YEAR, REDOING
THE FIRST HALLMARK CHANNEL CAT
BOWL.
WE ARE GOING TO HIGHLIGHT SOME
OF THE SENIOR CATS.
[APPLAUSE]
YOU DON'T GO THROUGH THE KITTEN
STAGE, NO SCRATCHES.
JUST A BEAUTIFUL CAT, COMFY,
COZY SPOT.
THEY ARE THE BEST.
THE ADULTS IN THE SENIORS -- MY
HUSBAND AND I ONLY GET UP THE
ADULTS.
THEY ARE THE BEST FAMILY
MEMBERS.
>> Rachael: IF YOU WANT TO
CHILL MORE AT HOME, GET YOURSELF
A LITTLE COZY FRED
!
THE KITCHEN
BOWL IS SUNDAY.
THE CAT BOWL IS SATURDAY.
ANYTHING NEW GOING ON THERE?
>> Beth: MORE CUTENESS.
I'M ON A FIELD, THEY ARE
CRAWLING OVER ME.
THAT'S MY JOB, DON'T HIM BEFORE.
WE HAVE A MARCHING BAND AT
HALFTIME.
COULD NOT BE CUTER.
WE HAVE SOME ADULT CATS WHO ARE
THE COACHES.
WE HAVE A ONE EYED ADULT COACH.
WE ARE REALLY SHOWING EVERYBODY
THAT'S AVAILABLE FOR ADOPTION.
WE HOLD THESE KITTEN BOWL
PARTIES ALL OVER THE
UNITED STATES.
AS A RESULT OF THIS BIG 11 PARTY
ON THAT DAY OVER 25,000 CATS AND
KITTENS HAVE BEEN ADOPTED SINCE
HALLMARK STARTED IT.
>> Rachael: AMAZING!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Beth: THAT'S WHAT IT'S ALL
ABOUT.
>> Rachael: LET ME TELL YOU,
BETH AND I AGREE ON THIS -- IF
YOU WANT TO BE A BETTER PERSON,
BRING HOME A CAT OR DOG.
ANIMALS MAKE YOU A BETTER HUMAN.
RIGHT?
>> Beth: MY HUSBAND AND I, FOR
SURE.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: THANK YOU SO MUCH
TO BETH.
I LOVE YOU, TOO, HOWARD.
THANK YOU FOR ALL YOU DO.
THANK YOU FOR ALL OUR FRIENDS AT
NORTH SHORE ANIMAL LEAGUE
AMERICA.
IF YOU WANT MORE INFORMATION
ABOUT THESE BEAUTIFUL KITTIES OR
ANY OF THE OTHER DOGS AND CATS
THAT NORTH SHORE ANIMAL LEAGUE
AMERICA HAS AVAILABLE, HAD TO
OUR WEBSITE AND WE WILL LINK YOU
GUYS THROUGH.
BE SURE TO CATCH BETH ON BOTH
THE NEW CAT BOWL, SATURDAY, FOR
BERRY SECOND, AND THE
KITTEN BOWL.
NUMBER 6!
SUNDAY, FEBRUARY 3RD.
OF COURSE, ON HALLMARK CHANNEL.
UP NEXT I WILL MEET YOU IN THE
KITCHEN TO MAKE SOME MEATBALLS
FOR THE OTHER JOHN, AFTER THIS.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Rachael: HEY, GUYS!
[APPLAUSE]
WELCOME BACK.
>> Rachael: HEY, GUYS!
WHAT I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU GUYS
WELCOME BACK.
TODAY IS ONE OF MY HUSBAND'S
WHAT I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU GUYS
ALL-TIME FAVORITES.
TODAY IS ONE OF MY HUSBAND'S
IT'S A GIANT MEATBALL THAT IS
ALL-TIME FAVORITES.
COOKED IN THE STYLE OF
IT'S A GIANT MEATBALL THAT IS
DUMPLINGS.
COOKED IN THE STYLE OF
WE ARE NOT GOING TO FRY THE
DUMPLINGS.
MEATBALL OR ROAST THE MEATBALL.
WE ARE NOT GOING TO FRY THE
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A BIG BATCH
MEATBALL OR ROAST THE MEATBALL.
OF OUR MEATBALLS AND COOK THEM
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A BIG BATCH
GENTLY RIGHT IN THE SAUCE.
OF OUR MEATBALLS AND COOK THEM
IT'S MY HUSBAND'S FAVORITE WAY
GENTLY RIGHT IN THE SAUCE.
TO EAT MEATBALLS.
IT'S MY HUSBAND'S FAVORITE WAY
WHEN HE WAS A LITTLE KID, THAT'S
TO EAT MEATBALLS.
SO HIS GRANDMA MADE THEM FOR
WHEN HE WAS A LITTLE KID, THAT'S
HIM.
SO HIS GRANDMA MADE THEM FOR
THEY ARE SOFT, THEY DON'T HAVE
HIM.
THE ROUGH EDGES OF THE CRISPY
THEY ARE SOFT, THEY DON'T HAVE
BITS.
THE ROUGH EDGES OF THE CRISPY
THEY REALLY TENDERED COOKED VERY
BITS.
GENTLY.
THEY REALLY TENDERED COOKED VERY
FOR THE MEATBALLS, WE ARE GOING
GENTLY.
TO MAKE A SMALL BASEBALL SIZED
FOR THE MEATBALLS, WE ARE GOING
MEATBALL HERE.
TO MAKE A SMALL BASEBALL SIZED
WE ARE USING 2 POUNDS TOTAL OF
MEATBALL HERE.
GRAND MEATS, A MIXTURE OF GROUND
WE ARE USING 2 POUNDS TOTAL OF
BEEF, PORK, AND FEEL.
GRAND MEATS, A MIXTURE OF GROUND
I USE HALF A POUND OF THE VEAL
BEEF, PORK, AND FEEL.
AND PORK.
I USE HALF A POUND OF THE VEAL
TO THAT I ALSO ADD PROSCIUTTO
AND PORK.
COTEAU, OR COOKED HAM.
TO THAT I ALSO ADD PROSCIUTTO
I PUT ABOUT A QUARTER OF THAT IN
COTEAU, OR COOKED HAM.
THE FOOD PROCESSOR AND GRIND IT
I PUT ABOUT A QUARTER OF THAT IN
UP TO MIX IN WITH THE MEAT.
THE FOOD PROCESSOR AND GRIND IT
NEXT WE ARE GOING TO ADD IN A
UP TO MIX IN WITH THE MEAT.
HANDFUL EACH OF PARMIGIANO
NEXT WE ARE GOING TO ADD IN A
REGGIANO AND GRATED PECORINO.
HANDFUL EACH OF PARMIGIANO
PARMIGIANO IS COW'S MILK,
REGGIANO AND GRATED PECORINO.
PECORINO HIS SHEEP'S MILK.
PARMIGIANO IS COW'S MILK,
THEY HAVE SALTY, DELICIOUS
PECORINO HIS SHEEP'S MILK.
FLAVORS BUT THEY ARE SLIGHTLY
THEY HAVE SALTY, DELICIOUS
DIFFERENT.
FLAVORS BUT THEY ARE SLIGHTLY
ONE IS MORE BUTTER, ONE IS MORE
DIFFERENT.
TANGY.
ONE IS MORE BUTTER, ONE IS MORE
THEN WE ARE GOING TO ADD IN OUR
TANGY.
BREADCRUMBS.
THEN WE ARE GOING TO ADD IN OUR
HOMEMADE OR STORE-BOUGHT.
BREADCRUMBS.
THESE ARE TOASTED ITALIAN
HOMEMADE OR STORE-BOUGHT.
BREADCRUMBS, PRETOASTED AND NICE
THESE ARE TOASTED ITALIAN
AND GOLDEN.
BREADCRUMBS, PRETOASTED AND NICE
SO THEY ARE A LITTLE NUTTY.
AND GOLDEN.
WHAT TO MOISTEN THEM WITH A BIT
SO THEY ARE A LITTLE NUTTY.
OF MILK.
WHAT TO MOISTEN THEM WITH A BIT
FOR THESE, I LOVE A LITTLE FRESH
OF MILK.
RICOTTA.
FOR THESE, I LOVE A LITTLE FRESH
THIS IS SHEEP'S MILK RICOTTA.
RICOTTA.
A LITTLE GARLIC.
THIS IS SHEEP'S MILK RICOTTA.
A COUPLE OF GOOD, FAT CLOVES.
A LITTLE GARLIC.
A LITTLE FLAT LEAF PARSLEY, OF
A COUPLE OF GOOD, FAT CLOVES.
COURSE.
A LITTLE FLAT LEAF PARSLEY, OF
A LITTLE FENNEL SEED OR FENNEL
COURSE.
POLLEN.
A LITTLE FENNEL SEED OR FENNEL
OR BOTH.
POLLEN.
THEY END UP TAKING KIND OF LIKE
OR BOTH.
SWEET CHEESY SAUSAGE.
THEY END UP TAKING KIND OF LIKE
NOT A BAD THING!
SWEET CHEESY SAUSAGE.
[LAUGHS]
NOT A BAD THING!
AND A LITTLE BIT OF NUTMEG TO GO
[LAUGHS]
WITH THE RICOTTA.
AND A LITTLE BIT OF NUTMEG TO GO
AND THE MILK-SOAKED BREADCRUMB.
WITH THE RICOTTA.
OF COURSE, SALT AND PEPPER.
AND THE MILK-SOAKED BREADCRUMB.
A LARGE EGG.
OF COURSE, SALT AND PEPPER.
BOOP!
A LARGE EGG.
A FAT DRIZZLE OF GOOD, FRUITY
BOOP!
OLIVE OIL.
A FAT DRIZZLE OF GOOD, FRUITY
EVOO.
OLIVE OIL.
THEN TAKE YOUR RINGS OFF.
EVOO.
[LAUGHTER]
THEN TAKE YOUR RINGS OFF.
YOU KNOW WHERE YOU'VE GOT TO GO.
[LAUGHTER]
YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHERE YOU'VE GOT TO GO.
[LAUGHTER]
YEAH.
JUST WORK THAT.
[LAUGHTER]
DON'T OVERWORK YOUR MEATBALLS.
JUST WORK THAT.
IF YOU FIND THAT YOU ARE NOT
DON'T OVERWORK YOUR MEATBALLS.
GREAT IT REALLY MEATBALLS THAT
IF YOU FIND THAT YOU ARE NOT
ARE LIKE SHAPES AND SIZES, USE A
GREAT IT REALLY MEATBALLS THAT
SCOOP TO HELP YOU MAKE THEM INTO
ARE LIKE SHAPES AND SIZES, USE A
LIKE SHAPES AND SIZES.
SCOOP TO HELP YOU MAKE THEM INTO
YOU CAN ALSO SCORE YOUR MEAT
LIKE SHAPES AND SIZES.
LIKE WHEN YOU'RE MAKING
YOU CAN ALSO SCORE YOUR MEAT
HAMBURGERS.
LIKE WHEN YOU'RE MAKING
MIX IT ALL TOGETHER, ESCORTED
HAMBURGERS.
INTO FOUR SECTIONS, AND SAY, "I
MIX IT ALL TOGETHER, ESCORTED
KNOW I HAVE TO GET FOUR
INTO FOUR SECTIONS, AND SAY, "I
MEATBALLS OUT OF THIS MUCH
KNOW I HAVE TO GET FOUR
MEAT."
MEATBALLS OUT OF THIS MUCH
I'M JUST GOING TO ROLL
MEAT."
MEATBALLS.
I'M JUST GOING TO ROLL
WHEN WE COME BACK, LET ME TELL
MEATBALLS.
YOU WHERE WE ARE GOING DOWN
WHEN WE COME BACK, LET ME TELL
HERE.
YOU WHERE WE ARE GOING DOWN
I HAVE ONIONS AND GARLIC
HERE.
SWEATING OUT IN OLIVE OIL.
I HAVE ONIONS AND GARLIC
TO THAT I'M JUST GOING TO ADD
SWEATING OUT IN OLIVE OIL.
STOCK, A JAR OF PASSATA, A CAN
TO THAT I'M JUST GOING TO ADD
OF TOMATOES.
STOCK, A JAR OF PASSATA, A CAN
WE WILL LET IT COOK DOWN A BIT
OF TOMATOES.
AND ADD THESE GUYS TO THE SAUCE,
WE WILL LET IT COOK DOWN A BIT
RIGHT AFTER THIS.
AND ADD THESE GUYS TO THE SAUCE,
[APPLAUSE]
RIGHT AFTER THIS.
♪ ♪
Digestive Advantage Probiotics
have a strong natural
protein shell.
So while other brands
may have billions of probiotics
many can struggle in stomach
acid.
Ours survive 100 times better.
Let our strength
help you stay strong.
♪♪
This Valentine's Day
take a moment to
create a moment.
♪♪
Let love unfold when you
add your heartfelt message
to a new Hallmark Paper
Wonder card.
WITH MY BLADDER LEAKAGE,
THE PRODUCTS I'VE TRIED
JUST DIDN'T FIT RIGHT.
THEY WERE TOO LOOSE.
IT'S GETTING IN THE WAY
OF OUR CAMPING TRIPS.
BUT WITH A RANGE OF SIZES,
DEPEND® FIT-FLEX®
IS MADE FOR ME.
WITH A RANGE OF SIZES
FOR ALL BODY TYPES,
DEPEND® FIT-FLEX® UNDERWEAR IS
GUARANTEED TO BE YOUR BEST FIT.
FOR ALL BODY TYPES,
I know it's hard Maddie.
But I promise,
it's gonna get better.
♪ ♪
(mom giggles)
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
The cold and flu fighting
machine.
You put in your machine.
Press the button to brew up
powerful relief.
To defeat your toughest
cold and flu symptoms fast.
NEW Theraflu PowerPods.
Press. Sip. Relief.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: OKAY, WE ARE JUST
FINISHING ROLLING OUR MEATBALLS.
IT'S THREE DIFFERENT TYPES OF
CHEESE IN THEM.
THE PECORINO, THE PARMIGIANO
REGGIANO, AND THE FRESH RICOTTA.
THEY HAVE BEEF, PORK, AND VEAL.
THE GROUND PROSCIUTTO COTTO,
LITTLE NUTMEG, GARLIC, ROSEMARY,
PARSLEY, AND THEY    THEY WERE D
SIZE.
A LITTLE BASEBALL SIZE.
MY HUSBAND LIKES A GOOD SIZED
MEATBALL.
HE LIKES TO TAKE TWO OR THREE,
CUT THEM UP, AND EAT IT BIT BY
BIT WITH THE PASTA.
GIVE MY HANDS A LITTLE RINSE.
BUCATINI IS HIS FAVORITE FOR
THIS DISH.
THAT'S BIG, FAT, HOLLOW
SPAGHETTI.
IT'S ACTUALLY KIND OF FUN TO
EAT.
THE SAUCE, AS I SAID BEFORE THE
BREAK -- ALTHOUGH I DID WAS LEAD
AND ONION COOKED DOWN LOW AND
SLOW AND OLIVE OIL, WITH A
LITTLE BUTTER AND OLIVE OIL IN
THE PAN.
AND A LITTLE CRUSHED OR CHOPPED
GARLIC.
LET THAT COOK UNTIL IT'S NICE,
SWEET MUSH.
DON'T BROWN THE ONIONS.
NICE AND SWEET.
THEN YOU HAD SOME STOCK --
CHICKEN OR BEEF STOCK -- ONE JAR
OF PASSATA, ABOUT THREE CUPS OF
TOMATO PUREE, IN OTHER WORDS.
AND ONE CAN OF SAN MARZANO
TOMATOES.
IF THEY ARE NOT, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO ADD A SPRINKLE OF SUGAR.
WE ARE GOING TO ADD A FEW LEAVES
OF BASIL.
WHEN YOU BRING HOME THE BASIL
FROM THE GROCERY STORE, KEEP IT
KIND OF LIKE YOU DO FRESH
FLOWERS.
TO INTO THE WATER EVERY COUPLE
OF DAYS, KEEP A PLASTIC BAG OVER
THE TOP AND KEEP IT ON THE
COUNTER, NOT IN THE FRIDGE.
THE COLD CAN BREEZE BASIL.
IT'LL LAST LONGER THIS WAY.
IF YOU PUT IN A PLASTIC BAG,
IT'LL BE LIKE A LITTLE BASIL
GREENHOUSE.
[APPLAUSE]
I'M GOING TO TEAR A FEW LEAVES
AND, BECAUSE WE ARE READY TO
DROP OUR DUMPLINGS.
GIVE THIS A LITTLE STIR.
THERE WE GO.
WILT IN A LITTLE BIT OF THAT.
I'VE GOT THIS ON MEDIUM HEAT.
AS I SAID, WE ARE GOING TO COOK
THESE LIKE DUMPLINGS.
SO YOU JUST DROP THE MEATBALLS
LITERALLY RIGHT DOWN INTO THE
SAUCE AND LET THEM COOK IN THER
THERE.
I KNOW, IT'S KIND OF FUN.
IT LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE GOING INTO
A MEATBALL SPOT.
[LAUGHTER]
THEY ARE ALL GETTING IN THE
HOT TUB.
[LAUGHS]
LOVELY.
NO I'M GOING TO PUT THE LID A
JAR TO TRAP SOME OF THE STEAM
COME OF THEM COOK GENTLY FOR
HUMANS BEFORE YOU MESS WITH THEM
AT ALL.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MESS THEM UP
BEFORE THEY FINISH COOKING
THROUGH.
WHENEVER WE COOKED PASTA, WE
SALT THE WATER GENEROUSLY.
WE USE THE SALTY, STARCHY WATER
TO MARRY THE SAUCE TO THE PASTA.
SALTER WANTED.
AFTER IT COMES TO A BOIL, SO THE
SALT DOESN'T SINK TO THE BOTTOM
AND SCAR YOUR POT.
GIVE THEM A SPIN EVERY COUPLE OF
MINUTES, AND I WAS COOK AT LEAST
ONE MINUTE LESS THAN THE PACKAGE
DIRECTIONS FOR AL DENTE, OR TO
THE TOOTH, BECAUSE YOU HAVE
CARRYOVER COOKING WHEN YOU'RE
TOSSING THE PASTA WITH THE SAUC
SAUCE.
IF YOU TAKE IT ALL THE WAY TO
WHERE YOU WANT TO EAT IT, IT'LL
BE OVERCOOKED BY THE TIME YOU
PUT IT IN THE BOWL.
THAT'S IT!
WE WILL COME BACK AND MARRY THE
PASTA AND THE SAUCE.
AND EAT IT!
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> WHAT NEW YORKER BECAME THE
FIRST WOMAN TO HAVE A NUMBER ONE
MOVIE, AND A NUMBER ONE ALBUM IN
THE SAME
I was on the fence about
changing
from a manual to an electric
toothbrush.
But my hygienist said going
electric
could lead to way cleaner teeth.
She said, get the one inspired
by dentists,
with a round brush head.
Go Pro with Oral-B. Oral-B's
gentle rounded brush head
removes more plaque along the
gum line.
For cleaner teeth and healthier
gums.
And unlike Sonicare, Oral-B
is the first electric toothbrush
brand
accepted by the ADA
for its effectiveness and
safety.
What an amazing clean!
I'll only use an Oral-B!
Oral-B.
Brush like a pro.
Woman:
This is your wake-up call.
If you have moderate to
severe rheumatoid arthritis,
month after month,
the clock is ticking
on irreversible joint damage.
Ongoing pain and stiffness
are signs of joint erosion.
HUMIRA can help stop the clock.
Prescribed for 15 years,
HUMIRA targets and blocks
a source of inflammation
that contributes
to joint pain
and irreversible damage.
VO: HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections
including tuberculosis,
and cancers, including
lymphoma, have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Woman:
Help stop the clock
on further irreversible
joint damage.
Talk to your rheumatologist.
Right here. Right now.
HUMIRA.
[music playing]
(Sashimi)
Psst. Hey, you!
The one with the designer dog
collar.
Wondering how I upgraded to this
sweet pad?
A 1,200-square-foot bathroom,
and my very own spa.
All I had to do was give my
human “the look”.
With Wells Fargo's 3% down
payment on a fixed-rate loan
and a simpler online
application,
getting into my dream home was
easier than ever.
Get your human to visit
wellsfargo.com/woof.
What would she do without me?
♪ ♪
>> WITH THE SIMULTANEOUS RELEASE
OF THE MOVIE "THE WEDDING
PLANNER" AND HER SECOND STUDIO
ALBUM, "J.LO," JENNIFER LOPEZ
BECAME THE FIRST WOMAN TO HAVE A
NUMBER ONE MOVIE AND A NUMBER
ONE ALBUM IN THE SAME WEEK.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: TO THE BUCATINI, A
LITTLE FEAR STARCHY COOKING
WATER.
I ADD A COUPLE OF DABS OF
BUTTER.
MY MOM ALWAYS FINISHED IT WITH
BUTTER, CHEESE, AND THEN THE
SAUCE.
A FAT HANDFUL OF PARMESAN OR
PECORINO OR BOTH.
THEN YOU GET THAT TO MARRY WITH
A GOOD STORY.
WE WANT THAT TO EMULSIFY A BIT.
GOOD, FRUITY OLIVE OIL AND/OR
BUTTER SO YOU'RE ADDING A LITTLE
THOUGHT TO THE PASTA.
WITH THE STARCHY WATER AND THE
CHEESE AS YOUR FOUNDATION.
MY MOM ALWAYS USED HER MUG TO
TRANSFER THE SAUCE OVER TO THE
POT.
I TOOK THE MEATBALLS OUTCOME OF
THE DUMPLINGS ARE PILED HIGH
THERE IN THE BOWL.
16 JOINT MEATBALL DUMPLINGS,
REALLY.
[APPLAUSE]
COOKED IN THE SAUCE.
AND HERE IS OUR BASIL SAUCE THAT
HAS LOTS OF FLAVOR, BECAUSE WE
COOK THE MEATBALLS IN AND WE
ADDED OUR STOCK, AS WELL.
TOSS IT TOGETHER, AND THIS IS
THE CARRYOVER COOKING WE WERE
TALKING ABOUT.
THAT'S WHY WE WANTED TO UNDER
COOK THIS A LITTLE BIT.
THERE YOU GO.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
I KNOW!
[LAUGHTER]
AND THERE IS MORE SAUCE LEFT AT
THE BOTTOM OF THE POT TO TOP IT.
YES!
THERE YOU GO, KIDS.
SPAGHETTI AND MEATBALLS!
[APPLAUSE]
GRAB A SNACK AND COME RIGHT
BACK.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
♪♪
WW Freestyle
is for everbody
who wants to eat the
foods they love
and still lose weight.
It's proven to help
people lose weight,
sleep better,
and feel happier.
Join for free
and get one month free
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: EVERYBODY WATCHES
MY SHOWS OVER THE YEARS KNOW
THAT I LITERALLY GREW UP IN
RESTAURANTS.
WE WERE ALWAYS IN THE KITCHEN,
AS WELL.
WORKING IN RESTAURANTS IS HARD
BUT IT ALSO BECOMES A PART OF
YOU.
THIS GIRL STARTED TO BE NEGATIVE
FOR ME, THOUGH.
THIS IS BABY ELEANOR, THAT IS
HER MOM, TATE.
TATE WORKS IN A PUB IN
NORTH CAROLINA WITH HER
BOYFRIEND, ELEANOR'S DAD,
PATRICK.
THEY TOOK ONE FOR THE TEAM BY
GOING IN DURING THE LATEST GIANT
SNOWSTORM.
THEY HAD TO BRING ELEANOR WITH
THEM, SO SHE BECAME KIND OF THE
HOSTESS WITH THE MOST US THAT
DAY.
IS THAT NOT ADORABLE?
EVERYBODY THAT WOULD THERE WAS
CHARMED.
THEY WENT INTO SERVE THEIR
COMMUNITY, TO SERVE THE PEOPLE
LOOKING FOR A WARM PLACE TO SIT
DOWN AND GET SOMETHING TO EAT
AND DRINK IN A STORM.
BUT SHE BECAME KIND OF THE
LITTLE ROCK STAR.
SHE'S ADORABLE.
WE HOPE TO BE ABLE TO TALK WITH
THEM.
THEY THEY ARE!
HI!
HI, GUYS!
HOW WAS SHE THAT DAY IN THE
STORM?
DID SHE GET FUSSY, OR DID SHE
SEEM TO REALLY ENJOY WORKING AT
SUCH A YOUNG AGE?
>> SHE LOVED IT!
SHE HAD SO MUCH FUN.
SHE GOT TO WAVE AT EVERYONE THAT
WALKED THROUGH THE DOOR.
SHE JUST SMILED THAT EVERY
PERSON THAT CAME IN.
EVERYBODY LOVED SEEING HER.
>> YEAH, SHE IS GREAT.
SHE'S HERE JUST ABOUT EVERY DAY.
SHE'S THE LITTLE PUB MASCOT.
>> Rachael: I LOVE A KID IN A
BAR!
IT'S FUN!
[LAUGHTER]
I REMEMBER WHEN I WAS A LITTLE
GIRL, THERE WAS A PLACE I STILL
GO TO TO THIS DAY CALLED THE
HARVEST IN QUEENSBURY, NEW YORK.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT IT WAS SO COOL,
BECAUSE THE GUY WHO OWNS THE
PLACE YOU STILL LET ME SIT AT
THE BAR AND EAT MY PIZZA WHEN I
WAS TEN.
AND I WAS LIKE, "HEY MAN, I'M AT
THE BAR!"
ELEANOR DEFINITELY HAS ME BEAT.
I'VE NEVER HUNG OUT IN A BAR.
YOU GUYS WERE TOLD YOU COULD
STAY HOME THAT DAY.
WHY DID YOU MAKE THE TREK IN
DURING THE STORM?
>> THE OWNER OF THE PUB, SHE HAD
BEEN DRIVING AROUND CHECKING OUT
THE ROADS BECAUSE THAT SNOWSTORM
FOR DOWN HERE WAS KIND OF
UNPRECEDENTED.
THE VOLUME OF SNOW WE GOT.
>> Rachael: YEAH, YOU DON'T
SEE THAT AMOUNT OF SNOW AND ICE
WHERE YOU LIVE.
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
SHE HAD BEEN DRIVING AROUND, AND
SHE SAID, "I WILL PICK YOU UP,
WE WILL GO TO THE PUB, MAKES
BREAKFAST, GET SOME
HOT CHOCOLATE."
AND WE WOULD SEE WHAT WE WANTED
TO DO.
WE WOUND UP CALLING OFF THE REST
OF THE STAFF, BECAUSE WE DIDN'T
WANT ANYONE ELSE DRIVING AROUND.
BUT WE ARE RIGHT DOWNTOWN, AND
ARE DOWNTOWN IS CONSIDERED FOOD
PORT IN THE SENSE THAT THERE IS
NO WALKABLE GROCERIES.
THERE IS NO GROCERY STORE
DOWNTOWN.
A LOT OF PEOPLE DEPEND ON THE
RESTAURANTS AND THE FOOD SCENE
DOWN HERE FOR THEIR MEALS.
A LOT OF PEOPLE DIDN'T HAVE
POWER.
SO WE THOUGHT, "HEY, LET'S OPEN
UP SO PEOPLE HAVE A PLACE TO GET
WARM.
THEY CAN GET A MEAL."
AND WE GOT SLAMMED.
[LAUGHS]
>> Rachael: THEY ALL CAME IN
TO SEE ELEANOR, TOO!
I BET SHE EARNED SOME TIPS!
[LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE]
>> SHE WAS THE LIFE OF THE
PARTY.
>> Rachael: THERE'S A REALLY
SWEET STORY THAT ATTACHES TO
YOUR STORY.
DO YOU GUYS KNOW THE BOUTIQUE
CALLED POLLIWOGS?
THE CHILDREN'S BOUTIQUE?
THEY SOLD FROM BABY CLOTHES UP
TO TWEEN'S.
A WIDE RANGE.
THEY THOUGHT YOUR STORY WAS SO
SWEET AND YOU ARE SO LOVELY,
THEY ARE IN GREENSBORO,
NORTH CAROLINA.
THEY ARE GIVING YOU GUYS --
WELL, ELEANOR, REALLY -- $5,000
TO THEIR STORE.
WE GOT ALL MY GOD!
>> Rachael: THAT'S A TIP!
ISN'T THAT ADORABLE?
>> OH, MY GOSH, !
>> Rachael: CHILDREN GROW
FAST, BUT GOOD LUCK KEEPING UP
WITH THAT!
$5,000 WORTH OF CLOTHES!
>> THAT'S AMAZING!
>> Rachael: ISN'T THAT SO
ADORABLE?
>> WOW, OH, MY GOD, THAT'S
CRAZY!
>> Rachael: WE WOULD BE HAPPY
TO PUT YOUR CHILD TO WORK HERE
IN NEW YORK, AS WELL!
[LAUGHTER]
VERY SWEET STORY.
THANKS, TATES, PATRICK, AND
ELEANOR!
WE WILL SEE YOU WHEN WE SEE YOU
COME EVERYBODY!
BYE-BYE!
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
Remember the way we
used to do things?
Hey man...
Like connect with friends?
Dig it!
Or get in shape?
Or sell a house
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
[crash]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.