♪ ♪
>> Announcer: TODAY, ON
"RACHAEL RAY"!
SHAKING UP HAS NEVER BEEN SO
MUCH FUN!
>> I LOVE YOU, HUGH JACKMAN, BUT
THIS IS A LOT OF ARM.
>> Announcer: FIRST,
DR. TRAVIS STORK IS DOING THINGS
BY THE BOOK AS HE REVEALS THE
SECRETS OF HIS DIET DICTIONARY.
>> I BROKE IT!
>> SEGMENT IS OVER, SORRY.
THANK YOU ALL SO MUCH, I'LL SEE
YOU NEXT TIME!
AND!
THEN...
>> WE LOVE YOU, THANK YOU.
>> Announcer: GO UP, UP, AND
AWAY WITH KATE WALSH.
>> IF YOU COULD HAVE A POWER,
WHAT WOULD YOU PICK?
>> TIME TRAVEL, BUT YOU HAVE TO&
BE INVISIBLE.
BECAUSE THEY DON'T WANT TO GO
AND GET TROUBLE.
>> Announcer: THEN, WANT TO
FEED A CROWD WITHOUT A FUSS?
IT JUST DOESN'T GET EASIER THAN
THIS.
>> LOOK AT THAT, IT'S CRAZY!
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: WELCOME,
EVERYBODY!
WE ARE HERE OBVIOUSLY WITH MY
VERY TALL FRIEND,
DR. TRAVIS STORK.
[APPLAUSE]
THIS TIME OF YEAR, EVERYBODY IS
TALKING ABOUT GETTING TO THE
GYM, ABOUT DIETING.
THE FIRST QUARTER OF THE YEAR,
EVERYBODY WANTS TO GET INTO THE
NEW YEAR AND BECOME THEIR BEST
SELVES.
>> Dr. Travis: THEY ABSOLUTELY
DO.
>> Rachael: WHAT HE ASKED HIM
TO DO TODAY WAS TALK TO US ABOUT
HIS DIET DICTIONARY.
WALK US THROUGH THE BASIC
LANGUAGE OF DIETING.
WHERE YOU WANT TO START, TRAVIS?
>> Dr. Travis: ARE WE READY
FOR TRUST, EVERYONE?
[APPLAUSE]
A FUN CLASS!
THE KIND THAT CAN HELP US BE
BETTER TO OURSELVES.
WE ARE GOING TO TALK ABOUT, WHAT
IS A CALORIE?
>> Rachael: OKAY.
>> Dr. Travis: WHAT DOES
METABOLISM MEAN, AND ALSO, WHAT
IS A MACRONUTRIENT?
WE WILL START WITH A CALORIE.
A CALORIE BASICALLY IS ENOUGH
ENERGY TO RAISE 1 KILOGRAM OF
WATER BY 1 DEGREE CELSIUS.
LET'S LOOK AT THIS -- THIS RIGHT
HERE IS OATMEAL.
>> Rachael: PACKAGED OATMEAL,
MY MOM HAS PACKAGED OATMEAL
EVERY MORNING.
COOKED FOR 65 YEARS, I GUESS SHE
IS TIRED.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Dr. Travis: OATMEAL IS SO
GREAT FOR YOU.
CARBOHYDRATE, LITTLE FIBER.
160 CALORIES IN THIS.
THEORETICALLY, IF I BRING THIS
COMPLETELY OFF, THAT WOULD RAISE
160 KILOGRAMS OF WATER BY 1
DEGREE.
>> Rachael: GOTCHA.
>> Dr. Travis: LET'S SAY YOU
EAT THIS MEAL, AND I'M GOING TO
PRETEND THAT YOU JUST ATE
160 CALORIES.
>> Rachael: WHAT IS THIS
DOODAD?
>> Dr. Travis: IT'S A BALANCE
SCALE.
>> Rachael: I BROKE IT!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Dr. Travis: SEGMENT IS
OVER.
SORRY.
THANK YOU ALL SO MUCH, I'LL SEE
YOU NEXT TIME!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: I BROKE IT AND I
FAILED THE QUIZ!
[LAUGHS]
>> Dr. Travis: YOU WANT TO
KNOW WHAT'S FUNNY?
ORIGINALLY WE WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE A LITTLE BUNSEN BURNER OUT
HERE.
AND I SAID, "PRETTY SURE WE WILL
BURN THE HOUSE DOWN."
AGAIN, LET'S THINK ABOUT FOOD IN
A POSITIVE WAY.
IT COULD BE YOUR MEDICINE, YOUR
ENERGY SOURCE.
>> Rachael: IT'S TRUE.
>> Dr. Travis: WHAT I'M GOING
TO DO A SHOW PEOPLE HOW OUR
BODIES USE THESE CAVITIES.
10% OF YOUR CALORIES ARE JUST
DIGESTION ITSELF.
>> Rachael: REALLY?
I'D BURN CALORIES EATING?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Dr. Travis: AND --
>> Rachael: THAT IS AWESOME.
[APPLAUSE]
LOOK AT ME, WORKING OUT!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Dr. Travis: I WILL GET INTO
THAT A LITTLE MORE IN A MINUTE.
YOU CAN BURN MORE CALORIES BASED
ON THE FOOD YOU EAT.
BUT 770% OF WHAT WE EAT --
GIVE ME A FEW MORE OF THAT.
70% IS JUST GOING THROUGH YOUR
DAILY LIFE.
EVERY DAY, YOUR BRAIN IS USING
ENERGY.
YOUR LIVER, YOUR KIDNEYS.
SO THAT IS WHAT WE NEED FOOD
FOR.
LAST BUT NOT LEAST -- AND THIS
IS THE IMPORTANT PIECE -- ABOUT
20% IS ACTIVITY.
AND PEOPLE WHO ARE INCREDIBLY
ACTIVE --
>> Rachael: PEOPLE WHO ARE
MORE ACTIVE OR SEDENTARY.
>> Dr. Travis: THAT'S WHAT IF
YOU ARE MORE ACTIVE YOU MIGHT
LOOSE SOME WEIGHT.
BUT IF YOU ARE NOT ACTIVE AND
YOU KEEP MEETING MORE AND MORE,
YOU'RE GOING TO GAIN WEIGHT.
THAT'S A BALANCE OF CAVITIES AND
CALORIES OUT.
HERE'S THE BLESSING AND THE
SKIES.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THERE ARE
CERTAIN PEOPLE WHO HAVE HIGHER
METABOLISM.
WHAT DOES THAT ACTUALLY MEAN?
THE RATE AT WHICH OUR BODIES
BURN CALORIES.
SOME PEOPLE GENETICALLY JUST
HAVE A HIGHER METABOLIC RATE.
OTHER PEOPLE -- BECAUSE THEY
WORK OUT A LOT AND MUSCLE BURNS
CALORIES MORE EFFICIENTLY AND
FAT, THEY HAVE A HIGHER ED ABOUT
THE GREAT.
THE NUMBER OF ENZYMES.
MY LAST BOOK, I TALKED ABOUT HOW
THE NUMBER OF GUT BACTERIA YOU
HAVE DICTATE YOUR METABOLISM.
>> Rachael: SEE IF YOU'RE
EATING A LOT OF PROBIOTIC FOODS
AND WORKING OUT TO BUILD MUSCLE
MASS, YOU COULD IN FACT INCREASE
YOUR METABOLIC RATE?
>> Dr. Travis: ABSOLUTELY.
A POUND OF MUSCLE BURN ABOUT TEN
TOES TODAY.
A POUND OF FAT BURNS ONLY TWO OR
THREE.
ONE OF THE EASIEST THINGS THAT I
DO EVERY SINGLE DAY IS EXERCISE
THOSE BIG MUSCLE GROUPS.
FOR INSTANCE, YOU COULD DO
BODY WEIGHT SQUATS.
GLUTES, QUADS.
>> Rachael: WEIGHT TRAINING IS
SO POPULAR NOW, RIGHT?
NOT TO GET HUGE MUSCLES BUT TO
BUILD MUSCLE MASS.
TO REPLACE THE FAT WITH LEAN
MUSCLE TISSUE.
>> Dr. Travis: THAT'S EXACTLY
RIGHT.
YOU WANT TO KNOW THE COOL THINGS
I'M DOING NOW?
I TURNED 47.
EVERY DAY, RAIN OR SHINE, I DO
MY AGE IN PUSH-UPS AND
BODY WEIGHT SQUATS.
BUT IT'S THE OPPOSITE OF --
NEXT YEAR I WILL HAVE TO DO
MORE.
>> Rachael: IT'S A TRAP FOR
ME, BECAUSE I'M 50 SO I HAVE TO
DO THREE MORE THAN HIM.
BUT WHATEVER.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Dr. Travis: THE IDEAS WE
ARE TRYING TO REPLACE THIS WITH
THE LEAN MUSCLE MASS.
WHAT'S COOL IS WE CAN USE FOOD.
YOU CAN SPEED UP YOUR METABOLISM
WITH FOOD --
>> Rachael: THIS IS THE PART I
FIND FASCINATING.
YOU CAN ACTUALLY USE FOOD TO
TRIGGER YOUR METABOLISM.
>> Dr. Travis: FOOD CAN
REALLY QUICKLY, I HAVE TO THROW
TRIGGER YOUR METABOLISM.
IT IN THERE -- SLEEP IS VERY
REALLY QUICKLY, I HAVE TO THROW
IMPORTANT.
IT IN THERE -- SLEEP IS VERY
>> Rachael: I SUCK AT THAT.
IMPORTANT.
>> Dr. Travis: JUST ONE BAD
>> Rachael: I SUCK AT THAT.
NIGHT OF REST CAN SLOW DOWN YOUR
>> Dr. Travis: JUST ONE BAD
METABOLISM.
NIGHT OF REST CAN SLOW DOWN YOUR
>> Rachael: MIND IS DRAGGING
METABOLISM.
SOME SERIOUS [BLEEP] THEN,
>> Rachael: MIND IS DRAGGING
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T HAD A GOOD
SOME SERIOUS [BLEEP] THEN,
NIGHT OF SLEEP IN A DECADE.
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T HAD A GOOD
YOU WANT ME TO MIX THIS
NIGHT OF SLEEP IN A DECADE.
TOGETHER?
YOU WANT ME TO MIX THIS
>> Dr. Travis: YEAH, MIX IT
TOGETHER?
TOGETHER.
>> Dr. Travis: YEAH, MIX IT
THIS IS MY CREAMY COOL CUCUMBER
TOGETHER.
DATE.
THIS IS MY CREAMY COOL CUCUMBER
THAT WE ARE GETTING INTO THE
DATE.
MACRONUTRIENTS AND WHY THIS
THAT WE ARE GETTING INTO THE
MATTERS.
MACRONUTRIENTS AND WHY THIS
THOSE ARE BASICALLY THE BUILDING
MATTERS.
BLOCKS --
THOSE ARE BASICALLY THE BUILDING
>> Rachael: SO THAT'S THE
BLOCKS --
DEFINITION OF A MACRONUTRIENT?
>> Rachael: SO THAT'S THE
>> Dr. Travis: IT'S THINGS
DEFINITION OF A MACRONUTRIENT?
LIKE FATS, PROTEINS,
>> Dr. Travis: IT'S THINGS
CARBOHYDRATES.
LIKE FATS, PROTEINS,
THROW THAT IN THERE.
CARBOHYDRATES.
WHEN WE EAT THESE
THROW THAT IN THERE.
MACRONUTRIENTS, OUR BODIES BREAK
WHEN WE EAT THESE
THEM DOWN.
MACRONUTRIENTS, OUR BODIES BREAK
WE NEED ALL OF THEM.
THEM DOWN.
WE NEED FATS.
WE NEED ALL OF THEM.
FOR INSTANCE, YOUR BRAIN NEEDS
WE NEED FATS.
FAST.
FOR INSTANCE, YOUR BRAIN NEEDS
RIGHT?
FAST.
>> Rachael: YES, YES.
RIGHT?
>> Dr. Travis: CARBOHYDRATES
>> Rachael: YES, YES.
HELP FUEL YOUR BODY FOR THE DAY.
>> Dr. Travis: CARBOHYDRATES
PROTEIN HELPS MAINTAIN MUSCLES
HELP FUEL YOUR BODY FOR THE DAY.
BETTER.
PROTEIN HELPS MAINTAIN MUSCLES
CREAMY COOL CUCUMBER TO.
BETTER.
THIS IS FROM --
CREAMY COOL CUCUMBER TO.
THERE IS GREEK YOGURT THERE.
THIS IS FROM --
I'VE GOT MINT LEAVES, DILL,
THERE IS GREEK YOGURT THERE.
GARLIC, CUCUMBER.
I'VE GOT MINT LEAVES, DILL,
CAYENNE PEPPER.
GARLIC, CUCUMBER.
SPEED ONE, WOW -- I JUST PUT A
CAYENNE PEPPER.
LOT OF THAT IN PERRY [LAUGHTER]
SPEED ONE, WOW -- I JUST PUT A
>> Dr. Travis: CAYENNE PEPPER
LOT OF THAT IN PERRY [LAUGHTER]
HAS CAPSAICIN ENDED.
>> Dr. Travis: CAYENNE PEPPER
SPICY FOODS HELP BOOST YOUR
HAS CAPSAICIN ENDED.
METABOLISM.
SPICY FOODS HELP BOOST YOUR
EVEN WITH THIS, HAVING SOME
METABOLISM.
GREEN TEA -- THAT CAN BOOST YOUR
EVEN WITH THIS, HAVING SOME
METABOLISM.
GREEN TEA -- THAT CAN BOOST YOUR
FOODS HIGH IN FIBER.
METABOLISM.
>> Rachael: I DRINK A LOT OF
FOODS HIGH IN FIBER.
GREEN TEA.
>> Rachael: I DRINK A LOT OF
SO I'VE GOT MINT, DILL.
GREEN TEA.
>> Dr. Travis: I WILL EAT MY
SO I'VE GOT MINT, DILL.
DIPS WITH BEAN-BASED CHIPS.
>> Dr. Travis: I WILL EAT MY
THE IDEA THAT THE PROTEIN IN THE
DIPS WITH BEAN-BASED CHIPS.
BEANS AND THE FIBER -- AGAIN, IT
THE IDEA THAT THE PROTEIN IN THE
TAKES YOUR BODY MORE CAVITIES
BEANS AND THE FIBER -- AGAIN, IT
EVEN BURN THIS.
TAKES YOUR BODY MORE CAVITIES
JUST DIGESTION ALONE, I BRING
EVEN BURN THIS.
SOME EXTRA CALORIES.
JUST DIGESTION ALONE, I BRING
>> Rachael: YOU GET MORE
SOME EXTRA CALORIES.
DIGESTIVE CALORIE COUNT OUT OF
>> Rachael: YOU GET MORE
THINGS THAT ARE DENSER OR MORE
DIGESTIVE CALORIE COUNT OUT OF
FIBER-RICH.
THINGS THAT ARE DENSER OR MORE
>> Dr. Travis: ED EVEN THOUGH
FIBER-RICH.
FIBER HAS "ENERGY" IN IT, SINCE
>> Dr. Travis: ED EVEN THOUGH
WE DO NOT DIGEST AND FIBER, YOU
FIBER HAS "ENERGY" IN IT, SINCE
NEED AS MUCH AS YOU WANT AND YOU
WE DO NOT DIGEST AND FIBER, YOU
ARE NOT GOING TO ACTUALLY GAIN
NEED AS MUCH AS YOU WANT AND YOU
WEIGHT FROM THE FIBER.
ARE NOT GOING TO ACTUALLY GAIN
IF ANYTHING, YOU WILL --
WEIGHT FROM THE FIBER.
>> Rachael: LOSE IT.
IF ANYTHING, YOU WILL --
IT MAKES YOU FEEL VERY FULL, A
>> Rachael: LOSE IT.
HIGH-FIBER DIET.
IT MAKES YOU FEEL VERY FULL, A
RIGHT?
HIGH-FIBER DIET.
DELICIOUS, RIGHT?
RIGHT?
>> Dr. Travis: IT DOES.
DELICIOUS, RIGHT?
[APPLAUSE]
>> Dr. Travis: IT DOES.
LAST BUT NOT LEAST, ONE THING
[APPLAUSE]
ABOUT FOODS THAT SPEED UP YOUR
LAST BUT NOT LEAST, ONE THING
METABOLISM, I'M ALSO THINKING
ABOUT FOODS THAT SPEED UP YOUR
ABOUT WHEN I MAKE A MEAL -- I
METABOLISM, I'M ALSO THINKING
WANT ALL THOSE MACRONUTRIENTS.
ABOUT WHEN I MAKE A MEAL -- I
>> Rachael: YOU WANT ME TO DO
WANT ALL THOSE MACRONUTRIENTS.
THIS?
>> Rachael: YOU WANT ME TO DO
OKAY.
THIS?
>> Dr. Travis: THIS IS AN
OKAY.
APPLE WALNUT BREAKFAST BOWL.
>> Dr. Travis: THIS IS AN
COTTAGE CHEESE, PROTEIN.
APPLE WALNUT BREAKFAST BOWL.
THE APPLE THAT WE ARE PUTTING IN
COTTAGE CHEESE, PROTEIN.
THERE, A NICE FIBER-LOADED APPLE
THE APPLE THAT WE ARE PUTTING IN
WITH NUTRIENTS, BOTH MICRO AND
THERE, A NICE FIBER-LOADED APPLE
MACRO.
WITH NUTRIENTS, BOTH MICRO AND
>> Rachael: A LITTLE APPLE?
MACRO.
>> Dr. Travis: LET'S PUT THE
>> Rachael: A LITTLE APPLE?
WALLETS THEY PRELOAD IT WITH
>> Dr. Travis: LET'S PUT THE
GOOD AS WELL AS FIBER.
WALLETS THEY PRELOAD IT WITH
CINNAMON, HELPED STABILIZE BLOOD
GOOD AS WELL AS FIBER.
SUGAR LEVEL.
CINNAMON, HELPED STABILIZE BLOOD
[LAUGHTER]
SUGAR LEVEL.
'S BE WHAT IT WENT THE WAY THAT
[LAUGHTER]
THE CAYENNE PEPPER BROKE OVER
'S BE WHAT IT WENT THE WAY THAT
THERE.
THE CAYENNE PEPPER BROKE OVER
>> Dr. Travis: WHEN I MAKE A
THERE.
MEAL TO GIVE IT ALL THE
>> Dr. Travis: WHEN I MAKE A
MACRONUTRIENTS.
MEAL TO GIVE IT ALL THE
I'M NOT COUNTING CALORIES, BUT
MACRONUTRIENTS.
I'M THINKING ABOUT, "OKAY, I'VE
I'M NOT COUNTING CALORIES, BUT
GOT THE WALNUTS --"
I'M THINKING ABOUT, "OKAY, I'VE
>> Rachael: THE QUANTITY OF
GOT THE WALNUTS --"
THE FOOD, NOT THE QUANTITY OF
>> Rachael: THE QUANTITY OF
THE CALORIE.
THE FOOD, NOT THE QUANTITY OF
>> Dr. Travis: EXACTLY RIGHT.
THE CALORIE.
WHEN YOU ARE THINKING OF
>> Dr. Travis: EXACTLY RIGHT.
CALORIES, METABOLISM,
WHEN YOU ARE THINKING OF
MACRONUTRIENTS, YOU DON'T HAVE
CALORIES, METABOLISM,
TO STRESS ABOUT IT.
MACRONUTRIENTS, YOU DON'T HAVE
IF TO REMIND YOURSELF, "WHY AM I
TO STRESS ABOUT IT.
EATING THIS MEAL?
IF TO REMIND YOURSELF, "WHY AM I
I'M EATING IT TO FEEL GOOD, TO
EATING THIS MEAL?
FEEL ENERGIZED."
I'M EATING IT TO FEEL GOOD, TO
>> Rachael: WHAT'S THE LAST
FEEL ENERGIZED."
TIP?
>> Rachael: WHAT'S THE LAST
IS THE CAYENNE INDUSTRY PAYING
TIP?
YOU ENOUGH FOR YOUR SUPPORT?
IS THE CAYENNE INDUSTRY PAYING
[LAUGHTER]
YOU ENOUGH FOR YOUR SUPPORT?
DO YOU EAT A LOT OF BLACK
[LAUGHTER]
PEPPERCORN?
DO YOU EAT A LOT OF BLACK
>> Dr. Travis: THAT'S A
PEPPERCORN?
NATURAL METABOLISM BOOSTER.
>> Dr. Travis: THAT'S A
I PUT ALL OF MY FOODS -- WHAT'S
NATURAL METABOLISM BOOSTER.
CRAZY, I GO TO THAI RESTAURANTS
I PUT ALL OF MY FOODS -- WHAT'S
AND I SAY, "MAKE IT NATIVE HOT."
CRAZY, I GO TO THAI RESTAURANTS
>> Rachael: YOU ROLL DEEP WITH
AND I SAY, "MAKE IT NATIVE HOT."
THE HEAT!
>> Rachael: YOU ROLL DEEP WITH
YOU GO THERE!
THE HEAT!
>> Dr. Travis: BUT I LOVE IT.
YOU GO THERE!
I PUT CAYENNE PEPPER ON MY EGGS.
>> Dr. Travis: BUT I LOVE IT.
>> Rachael: I LOVE HOT SAUCE.
I PUT CAYENNE PEPPER ON MY EGGS.
MY DENTIST FROM LOUISIANA, MY
>> Rachael: I LOVE HOT SAUCE.
MOM --
MY DENTIST FROM LOUISIANA, MY
WE LIKE HEAVILY SPICED FOOD.
MOM --
WE CAN TOLERATE A LOT OF HEAT.
WE LIKE HEAVILY SPICED FOOD.
I DIDN'T KNOW THERE WERE SO MANY
WE CAN TOLERATE A LOT OF HEAT.
HEALTH BENEFITS.
I DIDN'T KNOW THERE WERE SO MANY
>> Dr. Travis: THEY REALLY
HEALTH BENEFITS.
ARE.
>> Dr. Travis: THEY REALLY
LAST BUT NOT LEAST, WE'VE
ARE.
COVERED A LOT OF TOPICS.
LAST BUT NOT LEAST, WE'VE
THE MACRONUTRIENTS, THE
COVERED A LOT OF TOPICS.
METABOLISM, THE CALORIES.
THE MACRONUTRIENTS, THE
ONE THING I APPLAUD YOU FOR --
METABOLISM, THE CALORIES.
AND I CAN'T EMPHASIZE THIS
ONE THING I APPLAUD YOU FOR --
ENOUGH, I'VE TALKED ABOUT IN MY
AND I CAN'T EMPHASIZE THIS
BOOKS, ON "THE DOCTORS" -- FOOD
ENOUGH, I'VE TALKED ABOUT IN MY
IS MEANT TO BE ENJOYED.
BOOKS, ON "THE DOCTORS" -- FOOD
IT COULD BE ENJOYED AND ALSO BE
IS MEANT TO BE ENJOYED.
YOUR MEDICINE.
IT COULD BE ENJOYED AND ALSO BE
IN THE BACK OF YOUR MIND, ALWAYS
YOUR MEDICINE.
YOUR MIND YOURSELF WHEN YOU SIT
IN THE BACK OF YOUR MIND, ALWAYS
DOWN AND EAT THAT MEAL THAT IT
YOUR MIND YOURSELF WHEN YOU SIT
IS TRUE THAT IS NOT TO ENERGIZE
DOWN AND EAT THAT MEAL THAT IT
YOUR LIFE SO YOU CAN LIVE A
IS TRUE THAT IS NOT TO ENERGIZE
LONG, HAPPY, HEALTHY LIFE.
YOUR LIFE SO YOU CAN LIVE A
[APPLAUSE]
LONG, HAPPY, HEALTHY LIFE.
CHEERS TO THAT!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: WHAT IS COMING UP
CHEERS TO THAT!
ON "THE DOCTORS?"
>> Rachael: WHAT IS COMING UP
WHAT ARE YOU WORKING OUT OVER
ON "THE DOCTORS?"
YOUR STUDIO?
WHAT ARE YOU WORKING OUT OVER
>> Dr. Travis: IT'S ONE OF
YOUR STUDIO?
THOSE THINGS WHERE WE ARE 11
>> Dr. Travis: IT'S ONE OF
YEARS AND NOW.
THOSE THINGS WHERE WE ARE 11
I TELL YOU THIS EVERY TIME I
YEARS AND NOW.
COME ON YOUR SHOW.
I TELL YOU THIS EVERY TIME I
IT'S AMAZING HOW EVERYTHING IS
COME ON YOUR SHOW.
CONSTANTLY EVOLVING IN HEALTH
IT'S AMAZING HOW EVERYTHING IS
AND MEDICINE.
CONSTANTLY EVOLVING IN HEALTH
>> Rachael: AND YOU GUYS ARE
AND MEDICINE.
ALWAYS REEDUCATING EACH OTHER!
>> Rachael: AND YOU GUYS ARE
>> Dr. Travis: WE ARE!
ALWAYS REEDUCATING EACH OTHER!
EVERY DAY I LEARN SOMETHING NEW.
>> Dr. Travis: WE ARE!
AS I LEARN NEW RESEARCH OUT
EVERY DAY I LEARN SOMETHING NEW.
THERE, I LOVE SHARING IT WITH
AS I LEARN NEW RESEARCH OUT
THE AUDIENCE.
THERE, I LOVE SHARING IT WITH
BUT SO MANY COMPELLING STORIES
THE AUDIENCE.
THROUGHOUT THE SPRING.
BUT SO MANY COMPELLING STORIES
LITERALLY WHAT I JUDGE YOU DO
THROUGHOUT THE SPRING.
EVERY DAY ON THE SHOW IS SHARE
LITERALLY WHAT I JUDGE YOU DO
WITH PEOPLE MY OWN LITTLE TIPS I
EVERY DAY ON THE SHOW IS SHARE
USE MY OWN LIFE.
WITH PEOPLE MY OWN LITTLE TIPS I
IT HELPS ME AND I HOPE IT HELPS
USE MY OWN LIFE.
YOU.
IT HELPS ME AND I HOPE IT HELPS
>> Rachael: YOU DID A GOOD JOB
YOU.
FOR US HERE TODAY.
>> Rachael: YOU DID A GOOD JOB
WE'RE GOING TO BREAK WATCHING A
FOR US HERE TODAY.
CLIP.
WE'RE GOING TO BREAK WATCHING A
THANK YOU TO TALK TO HER TRAVIS
CLIP.
STORK.
THANK YOU TO TALK TO HER TRAVIS
YOU CAN CHECK YOU MET ON HIS OWN
STORK.
SHOW, "THE DOCTORS."
YOU CAN CHECK YOU MET ON HIS OWN
CHECK THE LOCAL LISTINGS.
SHOW, "THE DOCTORS."
AND HIS BOOK, WE HAVE DONE THAT
CHECK THE LOCAL LISTINGS.
SEGMENT HERE BEFORE, TOO.
AND HIS BOOK, WE HAVE DONE THAT
THERE'S A LOT OF GREAT ADVICE IN
SEGMENT HERE BEFORE, TOO.
THAT BOOK.
THERE'S A LOT OF GREAT ADVICE IN
CONGRATULATIONS.
THAT BOOK.
CHECK OUT THE CLIP.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> AFTER A DECADE OF HEALTHY
CHECK OUT THE CLIP.
ADVICE...
>> AFTER A DECADE OF HEALTHY
>> I WOULD CHOOSE A DIFFERENT
ADVICE...
PRODUCT.
>> I WOULD CHOOSE A DIFFERENT
THAT'S NOT FOOD!
PRODUCT.
>> MEDICAL BREAKTHROUGHS...
THAT'S NOT FOOD!
>> IT'S A MIRACLE,
Mucinex Cold & Flu All-In-One.
Fights...
...Sore throat, fever, cough,
sinus pressure,
chest congestion, headache,
nasal congestion, body  pain...
ALL IN ONE.
Did you really need the caps
lock?
Get tough on cold and flu
symptoms.
Mucinex Cold and Flu All-In-One.
Stronger is rebuilding
a newborn's heart...
and restoring a
father's faith.
It's standing tall
after one surgery...
not six.
Stronger is being
a typical kid...
despite a rare disorder.
Stronger is finding
it earlier ...
and coming home sooner.
Stronger is
seeking answers...
And not giving up,
until you find them.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: ALL RIGHT!
OUR NEXT GUEST IS NO STRANGER TO
OUR SHOW.
SHE HAS BEEN IN SO MANY GREAT
HEADS OVER THE YEARS, LIKE
"GREY'S ANATOMY" AND "PRIVATE
PRACTICE."
NOW SHE'S BACK, THIS TIME ON
NETFLIX AND A SUPERHERO ACTION
SERIES CALLED
"THE UMBRELLA ACADEMY."
TAKE A LOOK AT HER IN ACTION.
>> I SUSPECT YOU LIKE A
CHALLENGE.
WHICH IS WHY I'VE GIVEN YOU A
PARTICULARLY COMPLEX FIRST CASE.
ANYWHO, IF YOU HAVE ANY
QUESTIONS, I WILL BE RIGHT
BEHIND YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: PLEASE WELCOME
BACK TO OUR SHOW, KATE WALSH!
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
KATE THE GREAT!
>> Kate: HI, HIDE
!
>> Rachael: Q FOR GREAT IS
BACK OF A BLOG!
>> Kate: I'M SO HAPPY TO BE
HERE!
>> Rachael: I'M SO HAPPY TO
HAVE YOUR HOME!
IT'S BEEN WAY TOO LONG.
THIS KIND OF A DIFFICULT STORY
TO EXPLAIN.
CAN EXPLAIN THE THE SETUP OF
"THE UMBRELLA ACADEMY"?
>> Kate: THE UMBRELLA --
WELCOME OF THE WHOLE SERIES IS
BASED OFF OF A GRAPHIC NOVEL.
GERARD WAY WROTE IT.
HE IS FROM MY CHEMICAL ROMANCE
PRAYED HE WROTE A GRAPHIC NOVEL
CALLED "THE UMBRELLA ACADEMY" ."
GABRIELLE DID THE ART FOR IT.
THIS IS THE EASIEST WAY I CAN
EXPLAIN IT.
STEVE BLACKMUN, WHO THE SHOW, HE
USED TO RUN THE DRIVERS DULL MY
OR SURMOUNT "PRIVATE PRACTICE"
FOR A COUPLE OF YEARS AND THEN
HE ALSO WROTE ON "FARGO."
WE GOT TO WORK TOGETHER SEVERAL
TIMES.
HE CALLED ME AND SAID, "I'VE OUT
THIS CRAZY ROLE FOR YOU.
IT'S CALLED THE HADLEY."
>> Rachael: WHO DOESN'T WANT
TO GO TO WORK --
>> Kate: I KNOW!
THIS IS MY FAVORITE PART.
WE WROTE WITH JON HAMM IN MIND.
IF YOU WANT THE ROW WAS FOR A
MAN!
NOT JUST ANY MAN, JON HAMM!
HOW DID YOU STEAL THAT?
>> Kate: I KNOW, HAPPENS ALL
THE TIME!
IT'S A FIRST FOR ME.
I READ IT AND IT WAS SO GOOD.
THE WRITING IS SO SPECTACULAR.
IT'S A SCIENCE FICTION STORY
THAT DEALS WITH THESE KIDS THAT
WERE ALL BORN IN 1989, AND THEN
A GUARD TOOK THEM TO THIS
ORPHANAGE, THE
"THE UMBRELLA ACADEMY."
THEY HAVE SUPERPOWERS.
IT'S A WILDLY DYSFUNCTIONAL
SUPERPOWER FAMILY.
>> Rachael: IT'S LIKE A SUPER
SUPERSIZED SUPERPOWER
DYSFUNCTIONAL FAMILY.
[LAUGHTER]
EVEN IF YOU GET TO BE A
SUPERHERO AND YOU ARE SUPER
GIFTED, YOU ARE SUPER TWISTED AT
THE SAME TIME.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Kate: YEAH, SUPER GIFTED
AND TWISTED.
THAT'S A GOOD WAY TO PUT IT.
AND IT'S FUNNY, AND IT'S REALLY
BEAUTIFULLY SHOT.
I LIKE TO SAY IT LOOKS VERY
EXPENSIVE.
USE THIS WIDE ANGLE, SO IT LOOKS
LIKE --
IT'S REALLY EXCITING.
IT'S VERY COSTUME-HEAVY.
SO THE COSTUME DESIGNER AND I,
WE HAVE WORKED TO WORKED
TOGETHER CLOSELY TO DESIGN THE
LOOK OF THE HANDLER.
IT WAS ORIGINALLY WRITTEN FOR --
I SAID, "WHATEVER YOU DO, DON'T
CHANGE THE WRITING.
DON'T TRY TO MAKE IT MORE
FEMININE."
IT WAS SO WEIRD AND COOL.
>> Rachael: SO, THE HANDLER
CAN MANIPULATE -- WOULD YOU SAY
MANIPULATE?
YOU HAVE A GIFT WITH TIME.
>> Kate: YEAH, SHE'S IN TIME
MANAGEMENT.
THERE'S A LOT OF DIFFERENT --
IT'S A DIFFERENT KIND OF CHAIN
MANAGEMENT.
I CAN'T TALK TOO MUCH ABOUT
WITHOUT SPOILING IT.
BUT SHE DEFINITELY IS A BOSS
LADY AND SHE MAY BE A LITTLE
DANGEROUS.
[LAUGHTER]
SHE MIGHT BE A LITTLE.
YEAH.
>> Rachael: DID YOU HAVE A
REALLY FUN TIME WITH THAT?
>> Kate: HAD SO MUCH FUN.
AGAIN, IT WAS SO INCREDIBLE.
TO WORK WITH A FRIEND, IT WAS
JUST REALLY --
AND IT'S GOT A GREAT CAST.
ELLEN PAGE, MARY JAY
BLOCKAGE
>> Rachael: THIS IS NO JOKE.
THIS IS FOR REAL.
THEY'VE GOT A DEEP CHECK WITH.
THEY SEND IT WIDELY COME AS FAR
AS MY CONCERN.
I KNOW THIS IS A SILLY COCKTAIL
PARTY QUESTION, BUT IF YOU HAVE
A POWER -- IF YOU ARE ONE OF THE
X-MEN WHERE YOU WENT TO THE
ACADEMY, WHERE WOULD YOU PICK?
IF YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT IT?
>> Kate: YES, CLEARLY!
I FOUGHT FREE.
I WANT TO FLY.
I WOULD SAY TIME TRAVEL, BUT YOU
HAVE TO BE INVISIBLE.
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO GO AND
GET IN TROUBLE.
[AUGHTER]
I WANT TO GO, "WAS THAT LIGHT?"
>> Rachael: AND INVISIBLE TIME
TRAVELER, I DID THAT.
WE DO HAVE A CAPE?
>> Kate: WHY NOT?
IT'S EITHER GOING TO BE A CAPE
OR A TAIL, RIGHT?
>> Rachael: [LAUGHS]
I LOVE HER ANIMALS BECAUSE SHE
HAS A CAT AND A DOG AND THEY
LOOK --
THEY ALL GET ALONG!
IF YOU TAKE A
CAT AND A DOG, HAYING TO GIVE BE
THAT CHILD, PERHAPS YOU SHOULD
THINK ABOUT POLITICS!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Kate: I KNOW, IT'S AN
INTERSPECIES LOVE MATCH.
IT LOOKS LIKE AN ALBUM COVER.
>> Rachael: ARE THEY REALLY
ALWAYS SWEET TO REACH OTHER
CUSTOMERS WHICH CAME FIRST, THE
CHICKEN OR THE EGG?
>> Kate: PABLO WAS FIRST, AND
HE HAD HIS BROTHER -- BILLY
MOVED ONTO THE NEXT ROUND,
SADLY, LAST SPRING.
I VISITED WITH A COUPLE OF
THINKING ABOUT "CATTING UP"" AS-
I SAY.
>> Rachael: MY MOM HAS 15
RESCUE CATS IN TWO DIFFERENT
HOUSES.
NOT ONE OF THEM WILL PLAY WITH
ISABOO.
ISABOO JUST THINKS THEY ARE
SMALL DOGS, SO MY PIT BILL TRIES
TO PAY WITH THEM.
HER WHOLE FACE, SHE HAS LITTLE
DOTS OVER.
SHE LOSES THAT BATTLE.
>> Kate: ALL I POST OUR CATS.
[LAUGHTER]
BASICALLY COME MY SPINSTER HEAD
IS GUARANTEED
>> Rachael: SHE HAS A NEW
WHAT YOU THINK.
THE LESSON YOU WERE HERE, WE'VE
TALKED ABOUT --
SERIOUSLY, YOU ARE LAUNCHING A
FRAGRANCE!
A BOYFRIEND FRAGRANCE.
WHAT IS THIS HAND CREAM?
>> Kate: YES, THE HAND AND
BODY CREAM.
>> Rachael: NOTHING IS HELPING
THESE SUCKERS AFTER ALL THIS!
BEEN IN THE BOYFRIEND
TO LONG!
>> Kate: IT'S GOT A MEAL,
BUTTER, SUNFLOWER SEED OIL.
ALSO, HYALURONIC ACID.
WHICH I'M UPSET WITH BECAUSE I
GET VERY DRY SKIN.
WATCHING IT, DOING WHATEVER.
I HAVE DRY SKIN.
>> Rachael: PLUS COME IN AND
OUT OF WATER ALL THE TIME.
>> Kate: YEAH.
IT'S THE BOYFRIEND FRAGRANCE.
WE JUST LAUNCHED WITH IT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: I REALLY LOVE
THAT.
>> Dr. Travis: IT'S GOOD,
RIGHT
>> Rachael: I'M PUTTING
PERFUME CAME ON.
YOU OWN THIS.
TAKE IT BACK.
I'M JUST KIDDING.
CONGRATULATIONS, WE LOVE YOU.
>> Kate: THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: I LOVE THE WAY MY
HANDS SMELL NOW.
>> Kate: IT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
>> Rachael: I DON'T SMELL LIKE
GARLIC FOR 5 MINUTES!
WINNING!
"THE UMBRELLA ACADEMY" A
STREAMING NOW.
HOW MUCH TO BE LOVE STREAMING?
IT'S YOUR FRIEND!
WHEN I'M COOKING, WHEN I'M
WRITING.
CURLED UP ON THE SOFA WITH THE
POP.
I JUST LOVE SCREAMING!
I DON'T EVEN HAVE TO MOVE!
IT KEEPS STARTING OVER!
>> Kate: YOU HAVE TO FIGHT IT
TO STOP IT.
HAVE YOU NOTICED THAT?
"OH, MY GOD, I'M WATCHING A
MOVIE WHAT!"
I HAVE TO TURN IT OFF.
>> Rachael: IT'S AN ABYSS!
WAS TO GO IN, YOU CAN'T GET OUT!
[APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU.
STREAMING ON NETFLIX.
UP NEXT WE HAVE ONE OF THE TOP
CHEFS AND HE HAS BEEN TO THE
COUNTRY 'MOST FAMOUS HOUSE,
BEING THE WHITE HOUSE.
MANY, MANY TIMES, RIGHT AFTER
THIS.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Host: TOMORROW, CHEERS FOR
THE ONE ONLY KELSEY GRAMMER!
BIKO OH, KELSEY.
AT >> Host: THEN, PUT YOUR
HANDS IN THE AIR FOR CHEF ANNE
BURRELL'S ROAST CHICKEN AND MASD
POTATOES.
FORK AND KNIFE ARE OPTIONAL!
>> OH, YES!
>> Host: PLUS...
>> I WANT TO KNOW EVERYTHING.
HOST PANIC WE'VE GOT THE SCOOP
ON TIM TEBOW'S TOUCHDOWN
PROPOSAL.
>> I TAKE HER OUT THERE --
>> THROUGH A BOX THAT MY HEAD!
>> FRANKLY, ORDERING TAKEOUT
WHEN YOU COULD ROCK THIS AT HOME
WOULD BE CRAZY!
>> Host: THAT'S
♪♪
♪ 'Cos I know what it means ♪
♪ To walk along the lonely
street of dreams ♪
♪ Here I go again on my--- ♪
You realize your vows are a
Whitesnake song?
I do.
If you ride, you get it.
GEICO Motorcycle.
15 minutes
could save you 15% or more.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: SO, OUR NEXT GUEST
WENT VIRAL AFTER A PHOTO OF HIM
DRILLING AT THE WHITE HOUSE TOOK
THE INTERNET KIND OF BY STORM.
HE IS NOW KNOWN AS THE
WHITE HOUSE CHEF WITH 24-INCH
BICEPS.
[LAUGHTER]
I KNOW, RIGHT?
WHAT'S UP, HUGH JACKMAN AT THE
GRILL!
HE HAS SERVED OUR LAST FOUR
ADMINISTRATIONS.
TAKE A LOOK AT THE STORY ABOUT
HIM FROM INSIDE EDITION.
>> HE IS A BENCH PRESSING BEAST!
450 POUNDS, I WILL DO
250 POUNDS IN A DAY.
>> BUT ANDRE RUSH ISN'T JUST
BRAUN.
HE'S ALSO A CHEF AT
1600 PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE.
WHAT A REPORTER RECENTLY TWEETED
UP THIS PHOTO OF HIM ON THE
WHITE HOUSE LAWN, IT BLEW UP
THE INTERNET.
ANDRE HAS BEEN COOKING AT THE
WHITE HOUSE SINCE 1997.
HERE HE IS WITH PRESIDENT OBAMA.
HE HAS ALSO WORKED UNDER
PRESIDENT BUSH, AND NOW
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
WITH THOSE ARMS, ANDRE WORKS
WONDERS IN THE KITCHEN.
>> THIS IS THE BEEF TENDERLOIN.
>> ANDRE IS 45 AND AN ARMY
VETERAN.
THE DAY WE CAUGHT UP WITH HIM,
HE VOLUNTEERED TO PREPARE A
DELICIOUS MEAL FOR ACTIVE
SOLDIERS AND WOUNDED WARRIORS AT
THE USO CENTER IN VIRGINIA.
BECAUSE THANK YOU.
>> WITH ALL THE WORKING OUT HE
DOES, HE HAS A MASSIVE DAILY
DIET.
>> FOUR WHOLE CHICKENS, ABOUT A
DOZEN EGGS, A YOGURT OR TWO
YOGURTS, I WOULD DRINK TWO
PROTEIN SHAKES.
SOME MILK.
ABOUT TWO OR 3 GALLONS OF WATER.
>> A BIG MEAL FOR ONE REALLY BIG
GUY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: WOW!
LET ME JUST SAY -- I LOVE YOU,
HUGH JACKMAN, BUT THIS IS A LOT
OF ARM!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
SO, CHEF RUSH, NOT ONLY IS HE A
VERY BUSY CHEF -- HIS SCHEDULE
IS A LOT TO HANDLE.
NOT ONLY DO YOU GO TO THE GYM
EVERY DAY FOR YOURSELF, CHEF,
BUT YOU ALSO TRAIN PEOPLE IN THE
GYM?
>> Andre: I DO.
>> Rachael: SO HE MANAGES A
COUPLE HOURS IN THE GYM A DAY
TRAINING OF A PEOPLE, TRAINING
HIMSELF, AND HIS JOB AS A CHEF.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Andre: [LAUGHS]
>> Rachael: WHAT IS THE
GENERAL MOTIVATOR TO GET PEOPLE
TO CARE MORE ABOUT THEI HEALTH
AND WHAT THEY EAT?
IS THERE A GO-TO RULE FOR YOU?
>> Andre: KNOWLEDGE.
IT'S YOUR BODY, YOU ONLY HAVE
ONE OF THEM.
THAT'S JUST THE WHOLE PRINCIPLE,
AND THEN YOU GOT TO THINK ABOUT
YOUR KIDS.
BECAUSE THEY LIVE BY EXAMPLES.
>> Rachael: EXACTLY.
WHAT WAS THE LAST MEAL YOU
PREPARED OF THE WHITE HOUSE?
>> Andre: THE LAST MEAL I
PREPARED WAS THE MEAL THAT WENT
VIRAL FOR THE RAMADAN IFTAR.
IT WAS VEGETABLES, GRILLED
ZUCCHINI, SQUASH.
>> Rachael: SUPER HEALTHY.
>> Andre: SUPER HEALTHY.
>> Rachael: BUT IT WASN'T THE
VEGETABLES THAT MADE THE VIDEO
GO AROUND THE WORLD.
IT WAS THE BICEPS.
[LAUGHTER]
JUST TO BE CLEAR.
WHO ARE SOME OF YOUR FAVORITE
EATERS?
YOU HAVE SERVED FOUR
ADMINISTRATIONS.
YOU HAVE A  A FREE FOR A COUPLEF
PETER'S?
WHERE YOUR BEST LEADERS?
>> Andre: MY BEST LEADERS --
THE OBAMA'S.
>> Rachael: THEY ARE GOOD
LEADERS
!
AND I MET THEM BEFORE THEY WERE
THE FIRST COUPLE.
I MET THEM, BUT THE FIRST DAY I
MET THEM THEY WERE CHOWING DOWN
ON GIANT CHEESEBURGERS.
AS HEALTHY AS THEY ARE, AND THEY
ARE ALL ABOUT GOOD FOOD, THEY
BROUGHT THE GUARD AND THE
HONEY-ALL THAT.
I KNOW THAT MICHELLE KEEPS A
STASH OF MILKY WAY.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Andre: [LAUGHS]
>> Rachael: THEY ARE, THEY ARE
VERY GOOD PAY THEY HAVE AN
APPETITE FOR LIFE, I WOULD HAVE
TO AGREE.
DO YOU HAVE ANY TOP TIPS FOR US
SINCE WE HAVE YOU HERE, AND YOUR
BICEPS AS WELL?
>> Andre: OF COURSE, TOP TIPS.
[LAUGHS]
OF COURSE, MY GO-TO IS SIMPLE.
LABEL-READING.
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT COMES TO YOUR
KIDS AND YOUR HEALTH.
TOP TO BOTTOM, WE TALK ABOUT THE
COW INTAKE.
EVERYBODY HAS A CALORIE INTAKE
THIS DAY.
>> Rachael: ESPECIALLY -- THE
PACKAGE A SMALL, YOU ASSUME
THAT'S THE TOTAL CALORIE OF THE
ENTIRE PACKAGE.
>> Andre: THAT'S TRUE.
IT'S DECEIVING.
THESE NUTRITION'S, WHICH ARE THE
CHOLESTEROL, SODIUM, SOLD.
THIS ONE, FOR INSTANCE, HAS 20%.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT IT'S 100%
TOTAL, WHICH WOULD BE 4700
CHOLESTEROL.
YOU NEED TO ACTUALLY UNDERSTAND
THAT LIMITED HIS AS MUCH AS
POSSIBLE.
FOR MY GUYS IN THE MILITARY, 30%
OF A DAILY INTAKE.
THE MINIMUM YOU CAN USE IS THE
BETTER YOU ARE GOING TO FEEL
OVERALL.
>> Rachael: SEE WANT TO KEEP
ALL YOUR NUMBERS BELOW, NOT AT
THE MAXIMUM, FOR THINGS LIKE
CHOLESTEROL AND SODIUM.
>> Andre: EXACTLY.
>> Rachael: ASK YOUR DOCTOR
WHAT YOUR LEVEL SHOULD BE, I
WOULD THINK.
RIGHT?
AFTER START THERE.
YOU HAVE TO KNOW WHAT YOU HAVE A
PROPENSITY TO AND WE SHOULD BE
WATCHING.
>> Andre: OF COURSE ASKING HER
DOCTOR, AND ANYTHING ELSE, JUST
GO TO THE INTERNET AND FIGURE IT
OUT!
[LAUGHS]
>> Rachael: "THANKS A LOT,
DOCTOR!
">> Andre: A DOCTOR IS ALWAYS
FIRST!
[LAUGHS]
>> Rachael: AND THEN YOU GET
ENOUGH OF THESE NUTRIENTS.
ARE YOU GETTING ENOUGH OF YOUR
VITAMINS CUSTOMER FACING SURVEY
FOR RUE THE RECENT PARADE WHAT
IS THE FOOTNOTE?
>> Andre: THAT'S BASICALLY
JUST YOUR DAILY VALUE FOR WHAT
YOU NEED IN A DAY.
WHAT WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT.
YOU DON'T NEED TO GO OVER IT,
IT'S A GUIDELINE FOR YOU.
STEVE WANTS A RULE OF THUMB,
REALLY.
YOU HAVE ANOTHER TIP?
>> Andre: I DO HAVE ANOTHER
TOP TIP.
MY FAVORITE IS THE PORSCHE.
2,222 PUSH-UPS A DAY, I DO.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: A TIP IS SOMETHING
THAT'S APPLICABLE TO EVERYONE'S
LIVES!
[LAUGHTER]
I DON'T THINK THESE LADIES ARE
SUPER PSYCHED TO GET UP TO TRY
AND BUST OUT 2,222 PUSH-UPS.
>> Andre: [LAUGHS]
>> Rachael: WOULD YOU LIKE TO
SHOW US?
>> Andre: I WOULD!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
FORM FOR A PUSH-UP?
>> Andre: I WILL GIVE YOU
THREE QUICK VERSIONS TO REPEAT
SIMPLE, INTERMEDIATE, AND A
LITTLE BIT ADVANCED.
SIMPLE AS GOING TO BE A
MODIFICATION, KIND OF LIKE THE
PLANK.
JUST TO GET YOUR STABILIZATION
DOWN, YOUR CORE WORKING, FROM
HERE OR HERE.
HOLDING YOURSELF.
THAT'S IT.
NOT DOING ANY MOVEMENT.
>> Rachael: WHEN YOU PLANT
LIKE THAT, THAT'S WHAT BUILDS
YOUR CORE STRENGTH.
>> Andre: EXACTLY.
THE NEXT ONE IS GOING TO BE A
SIMPLE ONE FOR THE LADIES AND
THE MEN.
REGULAR -- CROSS YOUR LEGS, HOLD
YOUR LEGS.
ON YOUR KNEES, JUST DO A
PUSH-UP.
>> Rachael: HAVE A PUSH-UP.
SEE, THAT'S LOVELY FOR SOMEONE
WHO HAS A BUT AS BIG AS MINE.
[LAUGHTER]
BECAUSE I CAN LOWER IT DOWN.
NUMBER THREE?
[LAUGHTER]
FOR THE ADVANCE?
NUMBER THREE?
>> Andre: ADVANCES MY 2,222.
FOR THE ADVANCE?
YOU JUST GO AND YOU PUSH AND
>> Andre: ADVANCES MY 2,222.
PUSH AND PUSH AND PUSH.
YOU JUST GO AND YOU PUSH AND
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
PUSH AND PUSH AND PUSH.
AND KEEP PUSHING.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: OKAY, OKAY!
AND KEEP PUSHING.
>> Andre: I WAS GOING TO ASK
>> Rachael: OKAY, OKAY!
IF YOU WANT TO SIT ON AND DO
>> Andre: I WAS GOING TO ASK
SOME PUSHES.
IF YOU WANT TO SIT ON AND DO
>> Rachael: HELL YEAH!
SOME PUSHES.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: HELL YEAH!
OH!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[LAUGHS]
COME ON UP HERE!
I WANT TO SAY A PROPER THANK YO
THANK YOU!
UP NEXT, I WILL BE COOKING IN
THE KITCHEN.
I WILL MEET YOU OVER THERE FOR A
SIMPLE CHICKEN-BASED MEAT SAUCE
AFTER THIS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: WELCOME BACK.
IN OUR FAMILY, EVERY SUNDAY
NIGHT IS PASTA NIGHT.
REMEMBER THOSE SPAGHETTI
COMMERCIALS WITH ANTHONY RUNNING
THROUGH THE STREETS OF NORTH
BOSTON OR WHATEVER?
ONCE AND IT WAS THEIR SPAGHETTI
NIGHT.
FOR US, PASTA NIGHT IS ALWAYS ON
SUNDAY.
TODAY WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A
CHICKEN RAGU, OR A FIT, MEATY,
CHICKEN-BASED MEAT SAUCE.
WE ARE GOING TO SERVE IT UP WITH
SOME PAPPARDELLE, BIG, WIDE,
RIBBON-TYPE PASTA.
WE WILL BRING HOME A ROTISSERIE
CHICKEN, REMOVE THE SKIN AND THE
BONES, AND CHOP OR PULL THAT
INTO SMALL PIECES.
I GOT A NICE MEATY BACON THAT
I'M COOKING OFF TO GIVE IT A
LITTLE EXTRA SMOKY FLAVOR TO THE
BACKGROUND OF THIS DISH.
I WANT THE SMOKY FLAVOR TO
BALANCE THE SWEETNESS OF FRESH
FENNEL.
I TOOK ONE BOWL OF THE FENNEL,
RESERVE THE TOPS.
FENNEL, ONION, AND GARLIC GO
GOOD, ESPECIALLY WITH CHICKEN.
IF YOU COOK IT, IT'S FITTING TO
LEAVE LICORICE.
I WOULD CORE IT LIKE A WOODEN
APPLE, AND THAT CORBETT
YOU CAN OMIT IT AND IT WOULD BE
STILL DELICIOUS, BUT I LOVE THAT
COMBO.
THEY COMPLEMENT EACH OTHER SO
NICELY.
THE SMOKINESS OF THE BACON AND
THE SWEETNESS OF THE ONION AND
THE FENNEL TOGETHER.
IT'S JUST DELIGHTFUL.
DELIGHTFUL.
THAT SOUNDED SO PRECIOUS, RIGHT?
[LAUGHTER]
I ALWAYS COOK A LITTLE EXTRA
BACON THE WHENEVER THE RECIPE
CALLS FOR, EVEN IF IT'S MY OWN
RECIPE.
BECAUSE MY HUSBAND, JOHN, HIS
FAVORITE FOUR-LETTER WORD IS
"PORK."
I HAVE TO ADMIT, IF I'M STANDING
DIRECTLY NEXT TO BACON --
IT SMELLED SO GOOD!
AND THIS ALSO BE DELICIOUS ABOUT
THE BACON, TOO BREED JUST
WOULDN'T SMOKY AND FLAVOR.
IF I WERE AT HOME, I WOULD BE
BRINGING MY TONGUE IN MY FINGERS
FISHING BACON OUT OF THE PAN.
INCIDENTALLY, WHEN YOU COOK WITH
BACON, IF YOU ARE NON-CORE BRING
IT INTO A RECIPE LIKE THIS, WE
ARE RELEASING THE FLAVOR OF THE
DRIPPINGS.
BAKE YOUR BACON.
DON'T PUT IT IN A FRYING PAN.
ALWAYS COOK IT ON A SLOTTED
PANEL ON A WIRE RACK IN THE
OVEN.
THE FAT DRIPS AWAY, YOU NEVER
HAVE FLIP IT.
IT STAYS FLAT, IT DOESN'T CURL
UP.
IT COOKS MORE AND IT DOESN'T
MAKE A MESS OF YOUR STOVE.
375 TO 15 TO 18 MINUTES.
COOKING FULL SLICE IS A BACON.
IN GOES THE FENNEL AND ONION.
I'M GOING TO ADD LOTS OF FRESH
THYME.
AND A LITTLE GARLIC.
AND WE WILL LET THIS COOK UNTIL
THE ONIONS ARE NICE AND SOFT AND
TRANSLUCENT.
TILL THE FENNEL IS NICE AND
TENDER.
I'M GOING TO PULL SOME CHICKEN
PATE THAT'S NOT VERY PRETTY TO
WATCH, TAKING CHICKEN OFF THE
CARCASS.
I WILL MEET YOU BACK HERE AND WE
WILL CONTINUE ON WITH THE SAUCE.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
(MEG VO)
I can just suck up my
endometriosis pain...
Or I can...
(DIANE VO)
I can keep apologizing...
Or I can...
(SHERRY VO)
I can hope my pain gets better
on its own...
Or I can talk to
my gynecologist today!
(AVO)
You didn't choose to have
endometriosis...
but you can choose to ask
if ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA is specifically
developed for women
with moderate to severe
endometriosis pain.
In clinical trials,
ORILISSA was proven to reduce 3
common types of
endometriosis pain,
painful periods,
pelvic pain in between
periods,
and pain with sex.
Don't use ORILISSA if you are or
may be pregnant,
have osteoporosis,
severe liver disease, or are
taking drugs like
cyclosporine or gemfibrozil.
It may cause abnormal
liver tests.
ORILISSA may change your
periods, making it hard
to know if you are pregnant.
It does not prevent pregnancy.
Use birth control that does not
contain hormones.
ORILISSA may cause suicidal
thoughts or actions.
It may also cause bone loss.
Ask your gynecologist if
ORILISSA is right for you.
ORILISSA. Made for endo pain.
Cancer won't wait for
appointments to open up,
test results to come back,
or treatment plans to start.
At Cancer Treatment Centers of
America,
we make time for cancer
patients.
Time to answer questions,
relieve worries,
and turn indecision into good
decisions.
Because cancer won't wait,
and we don't think you should
either.
Call or go online anytime
to set up an appointment with
our team of cancer experts.
Cancer Treatment Centers of
America.
Appointments available now.
[Boy gasps]
For real cold and flu
protection
With Lysol, you can help
protect them from a real cold.
Lysol Disinfectant Spray
kills the #1 cause of the cold
and Clorox wipes don't.
Lysol.
What it takes
to protect.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: SO NOW WE'VE GOT
OUR FENNEL, ONIONS, GARLIC, AND
THYME COKED OUT WITH OUR NICE
SMOKY BACON IN HER BIG, DEEP
SKILLET.
ADD A LITTLE OLIVE OIL.
NOW WE'RE GOING TO ADD OUR
CHOPPED CHICKEN, PELLET WITH A
COUPLE OF FORKS OR WITH YOUR
HANDS.
THEN I JUST RUN MY KNIFE THROUGH
IT TO MAKE IT A LITTLE BIT
SMALLER.
WE ARE MAKING A CHICKEN RAGU.
TO GO WITH SOME PASTA.
IF YOU BRING THE CHICKEN FRESH
HOME FROM THE STORE, IT'S
PROBABLY STILL WARM.
IT DOESN'T TAKE LONG TO HEAT
THROUGH IT.
WE GET THE CHICKEN INCORPORATED
WITH THE SWEETNESS OF THE FENNEL
AND THE ONION!
LOVELY!
NOW WE ARE GOING TO ADD IN A
LITTLE WHITE WINE.
ABOUT A CUP.
LET THAT COOK DOWN.
WHEN YOU COOK WITH WINE, EVEN IF
YOU DON'T DRINK A LOT OF WINE,
YOU SHOULD AT LEAST INVEST IN A
WIND THAT YOU DREW THE FLAVOR
OF.
WHEN HE COOK WITH SPIRITS AND
WINE, WE ARE REDUCING THEM AND
CONCENTRATING FLAVOR.
SO DON'T BUY SOMETHING THAT'S
CALLED COOKING WINE IN THE
GROCERY STORE.
GO TO THE WINE SHOP OR YOUR
LOCAL LIQUOR STORE AND SAY, "I
DON'T WANT TO SPEND TOO MUCH, I
WOULD LIKE A REASONABLY PRICED
WINE.
I'M USING IT MOSTLY FOR
COOKING."
WE WANT TO SPEND A LITTLE MORE
ON IT AND HAVE IT BE SOMETHING
THAT'S PLEASANT.
BECAUSE YOU'RE CONCENTRATING THE
FLAVOR INTO YOUR FOOD.
DON AND I DRINK PRIMARILY RED
WINE, BUT I STILL BUY A DECENT
QUALITY WHITE WINE, BECAUSE I
COOK WITH IT SO OFTEN.
YOU LET THE WIND REDUCED.
WE ARE GOING TO DROP THE PASTA
NOW.
WE'RE GETTING CLOSE.
WE'RE GOING TO FINISH THE
SAUCE -- I ADD A LITTLE BIT OF
CHICKEN STOCK JUST TO GIVE IT A
LITTLE EXTRA LAYER OF FLAVOR AND
A LITTLE EXTRA JUICE WHEN YOU
ARE TOSSING THE RAGU WITH THE
PASTA.
AND JUST BEFORE WE SERVE IT, WE
WILL STIR IN SOME CREAM TO HELP
KEEP THE FLAVORS ON OUR TONGUE.
ON THE CREAM HIGHLIGHTS THE
SWEETNESS OF THE FENNEL AND THE
ONION.
WE ARE COOKING DRIED PASTA, IT
IS ESSENTIAL TO HAVE LEASING IS
IN WATER ITSELF.
AN ITALIAN COOKING, THE PASTA
WATER IS AN INGREDIENT IN THE
DISH.
WE SAVE SOME OF THE STARCHY
WATER, AND WE TOSS THE PASTA
TOGETHER WITH THE SAUCE.
LEND A LITTLE OF THAT STARCHY
WATER TO MAKE EVERYTHING
EMULSIFIED.
YOU SHOULD ALSO WAIT UNTIL IT
BOILS SO THE SALT DOESN'T SINK
AND SCRUBBED THEM BOTTOM OF YOUR
POT.
IT WILL GIVE YOUR POT THE
EQUIVALENT OF BAD SKIN ON THE
PERSON.
WE WANT TO UNDER COOK AND PASTA
OF CHOICE BY AT LEAST ONE
MINUTE, BECAUSE WHEN WE TOSS THE
PASTA TOGETHER WITH THE SAUCE IT
CONTINUES TO COOK.
I'M GOING TO COOK ABOUT A POUND
OF BEAUTIFUL EGG PAPPARDELLE OR
FETTUCCINE.
I LIKE AN EGG PASTA WITH US.
THE CHICKEN IN THE EGG.
GET IT?
[LAUGHTER]
REALLY, THIS IS ONE OF THOSE
DISHES -- IT'S A STURDY SAUCY
CONCERT WITH A PENNE OR
RIGATONI.
IT'S ALSO A LOVELY CONTRAST TO
AN EGG PASTA.
I WILL DROP THIS HERE, AND MEET
YOU BACK HERE IN A COUPLE.
WE WILL PUT THE WHOLE THING
TOGETHER.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
WW Freestyle
is for everbody
who wants to eat the
foods they love
and still lose weight.
It's proven to help
people lose weight,
and feel happier.
Join now at ww.com for
$0 Dollars
and get your first month free
Offer ends February 25th.
Woman:
I've been saying, "I'm fine."
But, really
I'm struggling to keep
up this brave face
to hide my symptoms
of depression.
I'm taking my antidepressant,
like we discussed.
But, I'm still
feeling depressed.
Is it just me?
Doctor: It's not just you.
Two out of three people
on antidepressants
may still
experience symptoms.
When added to an
antidepressant,
REXULTI has been proven
to help reduce
symptoms of depression.
Woman:
So I can stay on my
current antidepressant
and help build on
the progress I've made.
Hey, guys.
(Mixed greetings)
REXULTI is not for everyone.
Call your doctor about
unusual changes in behavior,
worsening depression,
or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants
can increase these
in those 24 and younger.
Elderly dementia
patients taking REXULTI
have an increased risk
of death or stroke.
Call your doctor if
you have high fever,
stiff muscles, and confusion
to address a possible
life-threatening condition
or if you have uncontrollable
muscle movements,
as these may be permanent.
REXULTI has been shown
to increase blood sugar
in some people.
Other risks are increased
cholesterol; weight gain;
unusual urges
or compulsive behaviors;
decreased white blood cells,
which can be serious;
dizziness on standing;
seizures; trouble swallowing;
and impaired judgment
or motor skills.
Now, I'm glad I talked
with my doctor
about adding REXULTI.
Feel better about
facing the world.
Pay $0 for your first
REXULTI prescription.
Details at REXULTI.com.
At Children's National,
stronger is caring for
a baby's heart
in the first 12 weeks
of pregnancy.
And a future when
prenatal pediatrics
leads to healthier children.
It's being the
number one newborn
intensive care unit
in the country.
And giving parents
peace of mind.
It's less recovering
in our bed,
and more jumping on yours.
Stronger is standing out
and standing proud.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
>> Rachael: IT'S A GOOD THING
YOU CAME BACK WHEN YOU DID,
BECAUSE OTHERWISE THERE WOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN A LOT OF PASTA LEFT
FOR ME TO SHOW YOU.
[LAUGHTER]
I WAS EATING IT RIGHT OUT OF THE
POT, IT'S SO DELICIOU.
HERE'S ABOUT A HALF A CUP OF OUR
SALTY STARCHY COOKING WATER.
A FAT HANDFUL OF PARMESAN AND
REGGIANO CHEESE.
I ADDED OUR CREAM TO OUR SAUCE,
AND NOW WE PUT ALL OF THE PASTA
SAUCE, THE CHICKEN RAGU WITH
BACON, CREAM, FENNEL, ONIONS,
AND GARLIC, BACK INTO THE POT.
TO TOSS EVERYBODY ALL TOGETHER.
AS I SAID, YOU WANT THIS TO
EMULSIFY ALL TOGETHER.
SO IT WILL CONTINUE TO COOK DOWN
IN THIS POT.
THAT CHEESE LOOKS SO LONELY --
LET'S NOT LEAVE HIM OVER THERE.
[APPLAUSE]
I LOVE THAT YOU ARE APPLAUDING
THAT!
[LAUGHTER]
OKAY.
"EXTRA CHEESE, HELL YEAH!"
[APPLAUSE]
IT'S FUN TO WORK HERE.
OH, MY GOSH, THERE IS SO MUCH
PASTA!
LOOK AT THAT!
IT'S CRAZY!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
OH, MY GOD, !
THAT REALLY IS A CRAZY AMOUNT OF
FOOD.
ALTHOUGH I'M TELLING YOU, MY
HUSBAND AND MY MOM -- THEY WOULD
BE NOTHING LEFT OF THIS.
NOTHING.
[LAUGHTER]
THESE ARE CALLED FENNEL FRONDS.
THESE LITTLE LACY THINGS THAT
LOOK ALMOST LIKE DILL WEED ON
THE TOP OF THE FENNEL.
SAVE A LITTLE BIT OF THAT.
THEY ARE VERY PRETTY, AND THEY
HAVE THAT LIGHT LICORICEY,
ALMOST BASIL OR TARRAGON-LIKE
FLAVOR TO THAT.
WE SPEAK OF IT OVER THE TOP, AND
IT'S JUST A GORGEOUS, SIMPLE
DISH.
YOU CAN MAKE IT ANY DAY OF THE
WEEK.
[APPLAUSE]
SO PRETTY, RIGHT?
COME ON!
UP NEXT WE'VE GOT SOME
ORGANIZING TIPS FROM 10-YEAR-OLD
TWINS.
TO KNOW THAT MUCH AT 10.
WOW.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
I know it's hard Maddie.
WOW.
[APPLAUSEBut I promise,
♪ ♪  it's gonna get better.
♪ ♪
(mom giggles)
I'm a close talker.
So I was excited about All-New
Colgate Total.
Its breakthrough formula does
more...
Wonderful.
Sensitivity, strengthens
teeth...
It kills germs through my whole
mouth..
I like your confidence.
Thanks Mr. Lee!
Now there's no such thing as too
close.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not.
Yes there is.
No, there's not!
Okay.
All-New Colgate Total.
Do more for your whole mouth.
I had this chest cold, but my
medicine kept wearing off.
(coughs)
Ah!
I missed you!
Then I discovered Mucinex.
One pill lasts 12 hours,
and I'm good.
Mucinex releases fast
and lasts 12 hours, not 4.
Let's End This.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> HI, RACHAEL!
>> I'M ELLIE.
>> I'M MARIN.
>> WE ARE FROM BETHESDA,
MARYLAND.
HERE ARE A FAVORITE TIPS AND HOW
YOU CAN ORGANIZE JUST LIKE US.
PUT THINGS INTO GROUPS.
CATEGORIES OF THINGS THAT ARE
THE SAME SO YOU KNOW WHAT YOU
HAVE AND HOW MUCH OF IT.
>> USING LABELS.
LABELS ARE SO FUN.
YOU CAN MAKE YOUR OWN AND
DECORATE THEM HOWEVER YOU WANT!
OR YOU CAN USE A LABEL MAKER.
>> WE ALSO LABEL ALL OF OUR
CLOTHES SO WE DON'T GET MESSED
UP BETWEEN BOTH OF OUR STUFF.
WE ALSO ORGANIZE TERRITORIES.
WE CATEGORIZE THEM AND WE ALSO
LABEL THEM.
TANK TOPS AND SHORT SLEEVE
SHIRTS.
>> WE DO IT WITH THE DESIGN
FACING UP SO WE KNOW ARE TO
SWITCH.
>> WE LOVE DOING THIS FOR TRIPS.
YOU DON'T FORGET ANYTHING AND
YOU DON'T OVERPACK.
>> YOU SHOULD ALWAYS HAVE A BIN
OR BASKET IN HER CLOSET SO YOU
CAN PUT THINGS THAT YOU EITHER
HAVE THAT ARE TOO SMALL OR THAT
YOU DON'T USE.
THEN WHEN SPRING CLEANING COMES
YOU CAN DONATE IT TO EITHER A
SHELTER OR SOME OF YOUR YOUNGER
COUSINS OR SOMETHING.
>> BYE!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: ELLIE AND MARIN
ARE HERE!
THAT AMAZING VIDEO, WE SAW IT
LAST SEASON AND I TOLD THEM
LITERALLY ON AIR THE FOLLOW-UP
TO THEIR VIDEO WAS TO CUT SCHOOL
AND HAVE YOUR MOM BRING YOU
HERE, AND HE COULD BE ON OUR
SHOW.
WE GOT THEM OUT OF SCHOOL!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
LADIES, I DIDN'T ASK YOU THE
LAST TIME WE SHOWED HER VIDEO
BECAUSE YOU WEREN'T HERE, BUT
WHY ARE YOU GUYS SO GOOD AT
THIS?
HOW DID YOU GET INTO IT?
>> WELL, OUR MOM IS A
PROFESSIONAL ORGANIZER.
SHE ORGANIZES PEOPLE'S HOMES FOR
A LIVING.
SO WE LEARNED IT --
>> Rachael: IT'S IN YOUR
BLOOD!
YEAH!
EVERY MOM AND DAD IN AMERICA
THAT WATCHES THE WORK THAT YOU
GIRLS DO, THEY ARE LIKE, "I WISH
I COULD GET MY KIDS TO DO THAT!"
DO YOU SHARE THIS WITH YOUR
FRIENDS?
TO TELL YOUR FRIENDS ABOUT THESE
TECHNIQUES AND STUFF WHEN YOU
COME UP WITH THIS STUFF?
>> YEAH, WE SOMETIMES MAKE
VIDEOS ON YOUTUBE.
>> Rachael: O COMICAL.
AND YOUR FRIENDS CAN WATCH.
RIGHT, RIGHT.
CAN YOU SHOW US A FEW MORE TIPS
ON HOW TO BE ORGANIZED?
>> SURE.
THE FIRST TIP IS TO PUT DOOR
TAGS UNDER CLOTHING HANGERS.
IT'S SO EASY AND IT SAVES SO
MUCH TIME.
BASICALLY, THEY ALL HAVE
DIFFERENT LETTERS AND THAT
REPRESENTS THE DAYS OF THE WEEK.
F IS FOR FRIDAY, SO I WOULD PUT
THIS ON.
SO I KNOW THAT THIS OUTFIT WOULD
BE FOR FRIDAY.
>> Rachael: DELAYED EXPLAIN
YOUR OUTFITS FOR THE WHOLE
BECOME ON A WEEKEND OR
SOMETHING?
THAT'S SO SMART!
IT WOULD SAVE GROWN-UPS A WHOLE
LOT OF TIME!
>> OUR MOM LOVES IT BECAUSE SHE
KNOWS WE TAKE SO LONG IN THE
MORNING TO GET DRESSED AND
EVERYTHING.
>> Rachael: IT NEVER CHANGES.
IT GETS WORSE AS YOU GET OLDER.
THAT'S A REALLY GOOD IDEA FOR
ALL OF US.
IT WOULD SAVE ME HOURS A WEEK!
WHAT'S NEXT?
>> THE NEXT TIP IS ORGANIZING
YOUR BOOKS BY COLOR.
THESE BOOKS ARE PICTURE BOOKS,
AND THEY ARE ORGANIZED IN MY
PERSONAL FAVORITE RAINBOW ORDER.
>> IT'S VERY APPEALING AND ALSO
IT'S REALLY FUN TO DO.
>> Rachael: AND IT JUST LOOKS
PRETTY IN THE ROOM.
>> YEAH.
>> I LOVE WHAT YOU DID WITH YOUR
STUDIO.
HE ORGANIZED YOUR BOOKS BY
COLOR.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: ONE MORE!
SHOW WAS OVER HERE.
WHAT'S THIS ONE?
>> THE NEXT TIP IS TO
ALPHABETIZE YOUR BOOKS.
BASICALLY WHAT YOU DO IS YOU
TAKE A PAINT STRIPPER, BUT YOU
CAN FIND ANYWHERE, AND YOU PUT
THE LETTERS ON THAT YOU WANT.
>> Rachael: IT'S THEIR LITTLE
LIBRARY.
DO YOU SEE THIS?
>> AND YOU DON'T NEED A
LIBRARIAN TO HELP YOU FIND YOUR
BOOKS.
>> Rachael: THAT'S HAVE THIS.
YOU GOT THAT A THROUGH C.
SO GOOD!
YOU GIRLS ARE BOXERS.
I DON'T WANT TO GET IN TROUBLE
WITH MOM
, BUT ANY TIME YOU HAVE VACATION
OR YOU WANT TO CUT SCHOOL AGAIN,
YOU'VE GOT A GIG HERE.
OKAY?
YOU ARE ALWAYS WELCOME AT MY
HOUSE!
ELLIE AND MARIN!
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US AND WE
WILL SEE YOU WHEN WE SEE YOU.
BYE-BYE!
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪