>> Announcer: TODAY, ON
RACHAEL RAY --
THREE CHEERS FOR THE WIN IN THE
LEE KELSEY GRAMMER
THEN, PUT YOUR HANDS IN THE AIR
FOR CHEF AND BURRELL'S ROAST
CHICKEN AND MASHED POTATOES.
>> OH, YES!
THAT'S RIDICULOUS!
>> Announcer: FORK AND KNIFE
ARE OPTIONAL.
PLUS --
>> I WANT TO KNOW EVERYTHING!
>> Announcer: GET THE SCOOP ON
TIM TEBOW'S TOUCHDOWN PROPOSAL.
FRANKLY, ORDERING TAKEOUT WHEN
YOU COULD MAKE THIS AT HOME
WOULD BE CRAZY!
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: WELCOME,
EVERYBODY, WELCOME!
I AM GETTING NECESSARY OBJECT
OUT OF THE FREEZER.
I HAVE PROPERLY CHILLED A PINT
GLASS.
HMM, WHAT IS RACH DOING CRACKING
OPEN A BEER AT THE BEGINNING OF
THE DAY?
I KNOW YOU'RE JEALOUS NOW,
AREN'T YOU?
[ACTUALLY, THIS IS A LEGITIMATE
PART OF MY
JOB TODAY!
NO KIDDING!
I AM PREPARING MYSELF PROPERLY
FOR MY FIRST INTERVIEW.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THE NAME OF MY
FIRST GUEST.
PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO OUR SHOW,
KELSEY GRAMMER!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Kelsey: HOW ARE YOU?
>> Rachael: IT HAS BEEN TOO
LONG!
YOU'VE BEEN AWAY FAR TOO LONG!
>> Kelsey: I KNOW, YOU WERE ON
THE OTHER SIDE OF TOWN LEST MY
WAS HERE!
>> Rachael: WE'VE BEEN LIVING
HERE FOR YEARS!
>> Kelsey: I THOUGHT SO, I'M
SORRY!
>> Rachael: TELL THE PEOPLE,
I'M NOT LYING.
THIS IS A LEGITIMATE PART OF MY
WORK TO!
LET ME TAKE A SIP.
>> Kelsey: LET ME TRY IT.
>> Rachael: IT'S VERY
REFRESHING.
THAT'S MINE, GIVE ME THAT!
>> Kelsey: IT'S GOOD!
>> Rachael: IT IS CRISP AND IT
IS BRIGHT.
>> Kelsey: THIS IS MY BEER.
>> Rachael: THIS LITERALLY HAS
BEER!
[APPLAUSE]
THERE, PROBABLY SIT DOWN.
ONCE I --
>> Kelsey: AM I GOING HERE?
>> Rachael: YOU GO THERE.
THANK YOU, MY DARLING.
>> Kelsey: OH, I LIKE YOUR
PANTS.
>> Rachael: I AM AN UPSTATE
NEW YORK GIRL.
THIS IS MINUTE UPSTATE NEW YORK,
CORRECT?
>> Kelsey: IT'S CURRENTLY
BEING MADE IN SCHENECTADY,
NEW YORK.
I'VE APPROPRIATELY        PROPE.
I BOUGHT THIS PROPERTY 27 YEARS
AGO, AND THERE WAS A PROPERTY
ADJACENT TO IT THAT HAD A HUGE
ON IT.
I TRIED TO WALK ALONG THE
PROPERTY AND I THOUGHT, "WHAT
SHOULD HAPPEN HERE YOUR?"
BECAUSE IT'S A VERY DEPRESSED
AREA IN NEW YORK STATE
NEW YORK STATE.
>> Rachael:
ECONOMICALLY-CHALLENGED.
>> Kelsey: I THOUGHT I SHOULD
DO MY PART TO REVIVE THAT AREA.
THIS IS OUR ATTEMPT.
WE ARE NOT FULLY REALIZED.
THIS IS -- WE ARE JUST A FEW
STORES.
>> Rachael: THIS IS A BABY
BEER.
>> Kelsey: WE'VE GOT EGGS AND
SOME CANS, AND OUR NEXT BATCH IS
BEING BREWED THIS WEEK IN
SCHENECTADY.
IT'S GOING TO BE OUT IN BARS AND
A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
AND HUDSON VALLEY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: THAT'S AMAZING!
>> Kelsey: AND ON THE CAN,
THAT'S A PICTURE OF ME.
AND THAT'S FACE NEXT TO ME
>> Rachael: HI, FACE!
>> Kelsey: PEOPLE ASK IF THIS
IS SOME SORT OF CHARITY, THIS
COLLECTION OF ANIMALS.
IT'S NOT.
WHEN I FIRST MET MY WIFE, KATE,
I NOTICED SHE HAD A VERY LONG
NECK.
SO I STARTED TO REFER TO HER AS
A GIRAFFE.
SO SHE IS THE GIRAFFE, I'M THE
ELEPHANT.
THERE ARE TWO BOYS.
AND ON TOP OF ME IS FAITH, WHO
IS AN OWL.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: THIS IS GIVING ME
CHILLS!
>> Kelsey: I'M SORRY, AND THIS
IS OUR PROPERTY.
IT WAS BORN IN THE CATSKILLS.
>> Rachael: I AM FROM THE
ADIRONDACKS.
I LIVE THERE STILL.
>> Kelsey: FANTASTIC.
>> Rachael: I CAN COME TO YOUR
BAR AND COOK FOR YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
AND YOU CAN COME TO MY HOUSE AND
BRING SOME BEER!
>> Kelsey: I WOULD LOVE IT.
>> Rachael: WE ARE ALSO HERE
TO TALK ABOUT "PROVEN INNOCENT."
I'M EXCITED TO TALK ABOUT THIS
BECAUSE WE SPENT THE DAY
RECENTLY WITH YOUR COSTAR,
RACHELLE LEFEVRE.
GIVE THEM THE CONCEPT.
>> Kelsey: IT'S A LAW FIRM
THAT REPRESENTS PEOPLE CONVICTED
OF A CRIME, AND THEY CLEAR THEM.
PROVEN INNOCENT.
THERE IS A B STORY IN THE SHOW
WHERE THE YOUNG WOMAN WHO IS THE
LAWYER IS PREVIOUSLY CONVICTED
OF A CRIME.
A MURDER.
I HAPPEN TO BE THE GUY THAT
CONVICTED HER.
SO I AM PERSONA NON GRATA IN HER
LIFE.
>> Rachael: BECAUSE SHE'S NOT
IN JAIL, SHE'S OUT.
SO HE WRONGFULLY CONVICTED HER.
>> Kelsey: HOWEVER, I STILL
BELIEVE SHE IS GUILTY.
SO THAT'S SORT OF THE TENSION.
THERE IS AN UNSOLVED CRIME THAT
KIND OF GOES ALONG THE STORY
LINE, AS THEY CLEAR AND FREE IF
YOU HAVE A PEOPLE.
IT'S KIND OF A NEAT IDEA.
ITS CURRENT IN TERMS OF PRISON
REFORM AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
APPARENTLY THIS GUY COME OVER 20
YEARS, NEVER CONVICTED A GUILTY
PERSON.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Rachael: YEAH, RIGHT!
>> Kelsey: IN ANY CASE, THE
SHOW WAS QUITE COMPELLING AND I
THINK THE PERFORMANCES ARE
REALLY GOOD.
>> Rachael: FUN TO WATCH.
>> Kelsey: I THINK SHE'S
REALLY DON'T LIKE ENGAGING.
AND RUSSELL, WHO PLAYS EASY IN
THIS SHOW, IT'S A NICE CAST.
I'M GONE AFTER 13 -- I SAID I
WOULD DIRECT SOME NEXT YEAR IF
THEY ARE FORTUNATE ENOUGH TO GET
PICKED UP AGAIN.
[APPLAUSE]
>> I KNOW YOU ALL THNK OF THE
VILLAIN IN YOUR STORY.
I ASKED YOU A QUESTION.
A MOTHER'S CHILD HAS JUST BEEN
MURDERED.
I HAVE, AT LEAST 100 TIMES.
I NEVER FORGET THE LOOK IN THEIR
EYES.
THE LOOK THAT SAYS THEIR LIVES
ARE NOW OVER, TOO.
THE ONLY THING I CAN DO TO MAKE
SURE I CAN STILL SLEEP AT NIGHT
IS PUNISH THE KILLER OF THEIR
CHILD.
>> WHAT ABOUT WHEN YOU GET IT
WRONG?
>> MADELEINE SCOTT IS GUILTY.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: THAT'S RIGHT UP MY
ALLEY.
THAT IS SO M, I LOVE THAT.
WHAT DO YOU LOVE TO WATCH?
IS THERE SOMETHING YOU LOVE TO
WATCH?
>> Kelsey: GOSH, I'VE GOT A
6-YEAR-OLD, A 4-YEAR-OLD, AND A
2-YEAR-OLD.
I DO WATCH A LOT OF TELEVISION.
I WATCH WITH A WATCH, WHICH IS
NOW YOUTUBE.
THEY WATCH SNIPPETS OF THINGS.
I'M TRYING TO GET THEM BACK TO
CONVENTIONAL FILMS.
I INSIST ON WATCHING "THE SOUND
OF MUSIC" ONCE A WEEK.
STUFF LIKE THAT.
AND THEY HUMOR ME.
THEY SIT WITH ME FOR ABOUT
20 MINUTES AND WATCH THE MOVIE
AN■>D THEN THEY START TO JUMP ON
TOP OF ME.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Rachael: WE ARE ALL
HARD-CORE, BACK IN THE DAY,
ORIGINAL GANGSTER "THE SIMPSONS"
FANS HERE.
I WANT TO KNOW HOW YOU GOT THE
ROLE OF SIDESHOW BOB.
>> Kelsey: WELL, THAT'S
INTERESTING.
I WILL DO IT AS QUICKLY AS I
CAN.
SAM SIMON, WHO WAS NO LONGER
WITH US -- GOD BLESS HIM -- USE
TO WRITE ON "CHEERS."
>> Rachael: NO WAY!
>> Kelsey: WHEN I WAS DOING
"CHEERS," I WOULD WALK ONTO THE
SITE AND SAYING -- "OH, THE GOOD
LIFE!"
[APPLAUSE]
IT WAS SORT OF MY THING.
BECAUSE IT WAS A GOOD LIFE, AND
I DID THAT TO REMIND MYSELF THAT
THINGS WERE EXTRAORDINARY.
HE CALLED ME ONE DAY WHEN I LEFT
THE SHOW AND HE WAS WORKING ON
"TRACEY ULLMAN."
AND SHE STARTED WORKING ON THIS
SHOW CALLED "THE SIMPSONS."
HE SAID, "WE'VE GOT THIS
CHARACTER CALLED SIDESHOW BOB.
DO YOU STILL SING?"
AND I SAID, "YEAH, SURE."
AND HE SAID HE SINGS A COLE
PORTER SONG, HE'S A SIDESHOW TO
CHRISTIE
KRUSTY THE CLOWN, AND HE HAS
NEVER SAID ANYTHING.
I USE THE WORK WITH A GUY NAMED
ELLIS WAS AN ACTOR AND PRODUCER
OF BROADWAY SHOWS HERE IN
NEW YORK CITY.
SOME PEOPLE MAY REMEMBER HIM OR
NOT.
HE WAS MARRIED FOR A WHILE TO
ROSEMARY HARRIS.
THIS BECOMES A VERY CONFUSING
STORY.
I USED TO WORK FOR HIM PAINTING
HIS APARTMENT AND THEN PAINTING
HIS OFFICES, AS WELL.
IN THE EVENING --
>> Rachael: SUCH A RENAISSANCE
MAN.
[LAUGHS]
>> Kelsey: YES, I WAS PAINTING
MURALS.
[LAUGHS]
IN THE EVENINGS HE WOULD SIT
DOWN WHEN WE WOULD COME BACK
FROM WORK AND SAY, "OH, KELSEY.
OH."
THIS AND THAT.
AND I THOUGHT ABOUT THAT GUY.
"I'M GOING TO DO HIM ONE DAY."
AND YOU SAY THIS.
ROSEMARY HARRIS HAD MARRIED
SOMEONE ELSE AND HAD A BABY, AND
HE SAID THIS LINE.
"OH, KELSEY -- THAT BABY SHOULD
HAVE BEEN MINE."
AND I THOUGHT, BOY, THAT IS JUST
SO MEMORABLE.
BOB, AND THE CAPPER ON THE STORY
IS I WAS AUDITIONING YOUNG WOMEN
FOR THE SHOW "BOSTON" I DID IN
CHICAGO ABOUT SEVEN YEARS AGO.
A GIRL CAME IN.
LOVELY, GIVE A GREAT
PERFORMANCE.
SHE TURNED TO ME AND SAID, "BY
THE WAY, I AM THAT BABY."
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: I LOVED "BOSTON."
BY THE WAY, I WAS JUST
COMPLEMENTING KELSEY.
AND ALL OF THE FAKE THINGS
YOU'VE BEEN, WHICH FAKE
PROFESSION DO THINK HE WOULD
HAVE BEEN QUITE GOOD AT IN REAL
LIFE?
>> Kelsey: I THINK I COULD
HAVE BEEN QUITE A GOOD MAYOR OF
CHICAGO.
I WAS A VERY DASTARDLY EVIL MAN
AS TOM.
THAT WAS MY FAVORITE ROLLOVER.
FRASER'S NUMBER TWO, BUT THAT
WAS MY FAVORITE ROLE.
HE WAS A FANTASTIC PAIR OF
GEORGIA PLAY.
WAS EVEN MORE FUN IS WE PICKED
UP OUR FAMILY FROM THE AIRPORT
ONE DAY, AND WE HAD NO CAR
SEATS.
WE --
OH, DEAR GOD, WHAT WOULD WE DO
CUSTOM WORK AND THE KIDS WERE
STANDING UP IN THE BACK.
I MADE AN INCORRECT RIGHT TURN
AND THERE IS A COP.
SO THEY PULLED ME OVER.
THE ONE GUY IS SORT OF AN EAGER
BEAVER YOUNG GUY.
THERE'S ANOTHER OLDER COP RIDING
ALONG.
HE STARTS TO LOOK AT ME, THE
OLDER COP LOOKS UP AND HE SAYS,
"DRIVER'S LICENSE, REGISTRATION
PLEASE."
SO I START DOING THE BIT.
AND THE OLDER COP WALKS UP AND
SAYS, "HOW ARE YOU DOING,
MR. MAYOR?"
>> Rachael: [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE]
THAT'S EPIC!
>> Kelsey: AND HE SAID,
"THERE'S NO PROBLEM HERE.
MOVE ALONG, MOVE ALONG."
>> Rachael: I LOVE KNOWING
THAT, THAT IT CAN GET YOU OUT OF
TROUBLE WITH THE LAW!
"PROVEN INNOCENT" AIRS FRIDAYS
AT 9:00.
I, FOR ONE, WILL BE WATCHING.
IT AIRS ON FOX.
THIS IS SUCH A HAPPY DAY COME ON
MY FACE JUST HURTS.
I'M HAPPY TO WELCOME MY SWEET
FRIEND, ANNE BURRELL.
SHE'S IN THE KITCHEN COMING UP.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Host: TOMORROW, SUPERSTAR
SHAFT DANIEL HAS A BRAND-NEW
TEAM
>> IT SMELLS AMAZING!
>> Host: A TEAM OF ROBOTS
COOKING UP MADE-TO-ORDER MEALS
IN JUST MINUTES.
>> OH!
THAT'S EXCITING!
>> Host: THEN, SEEMS LIKE OLD
TIMES WHEN TRISHA YEARWOOD POPS
IN.
>> WE WERE TALKING ABOUT RETRO
TV SHOWS.
AND SHE WAS LIKE, "REMEMBER
FRIENDS?"
>> THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO!
>> Host: PLUS, ILLUSIONIST
MICHAEL CARBON ARO.
>> RACHAEL!
OPEN YOUR PALM.
>> Host: AND, A MAGICAL
SPRINGTIME PASTA.
JUST 30 MINUTES
Mucinex Cold & Flu All-In-One.
Fights...
...Sore throat, fever, cough,
sinus pressure,
chest congestion, headache,
nasal congestion, body  pain...
ALL IN ONE.
Did you really need the caps
lock?
Get tough on cold and flu
symptoms.
Mucinex Cold and Flu All-In-One.
[phone ringing]
Remember the way we
used to do things?
Hey man...
Like connect with friends?
Dig it!
Or get in shape?
Or sell a house
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
[crash]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: ALL RIGHT, MY NEXT
GUEST IS SHOWING OFF ONE RECIPE
THAT EVERYONE SHOULD KNOW HOW TO
MAKE NO MATTER THEIR SKILL
LEVEL.
SHE IS REALLY GOOD AT THAT.
SHE DOES IT QUITE OFTEN ON A
LITTLE SHOW CALLED "WORST COOKS
IN AMERICA."
CHECK HER OUT AN ACTION.
>> I AM GOING TO BE MAKING A
CORNED BEEF AND POTATO HASH
TODAY WITH ONIONS AND BELL
PEPPERS.
WE NEED TO DICE THE POTATOES.
SLICES, STICKS, DICES.
WE WILL PUT THESE IN MY WATER
THEN BTB, AND RTS.
BRING TO BOIL, REDUCE TO A
SIMMER.
BTB, RTS.
>> BTB, RTS.
>> Rachael: [LAUGHS]
[APPLAUSE]
PLEASE WELCOME, CHEF
ANNE BURRELL.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
I WAS LAUGHING BECAUSE THAT SHE
WAS VERY FAMILIAR TO ME.
CHEF AND HAS ALLOWED ME
GRACIOUSLY TO PARTICIPATE IN
THAT SHOW.
IF YOU THINK THAT'S NOT REAL,
TRUST ME -- IT ROLLS DEEP WITH
THOSE COOKS.
THEY ARE BAD!
[LAUGHTER]
IT'S A BAD!
>> Anne: WE HAVE HAD AN
AMAZING CRAZY CAST OF
CHARACTERS.
WHAT I LIKE TO CALL MY "LOVABLE
LOSERS."
>> Rachael: [LAUGHS]
>> Anne: TELL EVERYONE -- THE
VERY FIRST DAY, THE FIRST
5 MINUTES INTO SHOOTING HIM HE
LOOKED AT ME AND YOU WERE LIKE,
"AND, WHAT DID YOU GET ME INTO?
I THOUGHT WE WERE FRIENDS!"
>> Rachael: IT WAS HORRIFYING!
THIS VERY SWEET MAN BEGGED US A
CASSEROLE OF TUNA, AMERICAN
CHEESE, AND A JAR OF JELLY!
AND MAYONNAISE!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Anne: I'VE TOLD THE STORY A
LOT THIS YEAR ABOUT YOU AND HOW
MUCH YOU HATE HOT MAYONNAISE.
SO IT WAS LIKE TUNA FISH, TONS
OF MAYONNAISE, AMERICAN CHEESE,
RASPBERRY JELLY, BAKED IN THE
OVEN AND JUST -- LIKE, IT WAS --
AND YOU WERE LIKE, "I'M NOT
EATING THAT."
[LAUGHTER]
>> Rachael: ANYWAY, SHE IS
TOUGH.
HOW'S IT GOING THIS SEASON?
HAVE YOU COME A LONG WAY?
>> Anne: YES.
THERE WAS NOWHERE TO GO BUT UP!
OH, MY GOD.
>> Rachael: THE MILK BOILED
OVER.
SERIOUSLY, THE WHOLE PREMISE OF
THE SHOW IS ACTUALLY A VERY
LOVING ONE THAT ANYONE CAN BE
EMPOWERED IN THE KITCHEN TO
COOK.
THE BASICS AND THEN SOME.
BY THE END OF EACH ROUND OF
WORST COOKS, THESE PEOPLE ARE
PRODUCING MORE THAN RESTAURANT
QUALITY FOOD.
FIND RESTAURANT QUALITY FOOD.
[APPLAUSE]
SHE SHOWS PEOPLE HOW TO MAKE ONE
BASIC THING AND DO IT REALLY
WELL.
WHAT ARE WE TACKLING TODAY?
BE >> Anne: WE ARE DOING A
ROASTED CHICKEN AND MASHED
POTATOES.
>> Rachael: THE GO TO SUPPER.
>> Anne: I LOVE A CHICKEN DID
IT.
I LOVE ROASTED CHICKEN DINNER
BECAUSE IT FEELS LIKE IT'S FANCY
A LITTLE BIT.
THE THING IS, A ROASTED CHICKEN
IS REALLY EASY TO DO BADLY.
>> Rachael: YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> Anne: WHEN YOU DO IT WELL,
YOU ARE LIKE, "BOOM!
I JUST ROCKED IT."
>> Rachael: IT'S EMPOWERING.
AND YOU ARE --
>> Anne: I LOVE A MASHED
POTATO.
>> Rachael: HER MASHED
POTATOES ARE LIKE A CLOUD, A
DREAM.
>> Anne: I DON'T USUALLY COOK
WITH BUTTER WERE HEAVY CREAM
UNTIL I GET TO MASHED POTATOES,
AND THEN IT'S LIKE BUTTER AND
CREAM HELD TOGETHER BY A LITTLE
BIT OF POTATO.
[LAUGHTER]
THE THING ABOUT A ROASTED
CHICKEN -- SOMETIMES PEOPLE LOOK
AT IT AND GET THEY ARE LIKE,
"IT'S A LITTLE BIT SCARY.
DO YOU WANT TO GRATE THESE GUYS?
>> Rachael: SURE, BABY.
>> Anne: THAT'S SPICY.
>> Rachael: LITERALLY A
MOUNTAIN OF RED PEPPER.
WE WILL USE LIKE THAT MUCH.
>> Anne: IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
A CRAZY THING TO DO.
THERE'S A FEW SIMPLE RULES.
ONCE YOU GET THOSE DOWN, IT IS
LIKE -- YOU GET HOME FROM WORK
WITH YOUR CHICKEN AND YOUR
HERBS.
WE HAVE ROSEMARY AND SAGE AND A
LITTLE GARLIC THAT I'M MAKING,
JUST AN HERB PASTE.
AND WE WILL SLIP THIS RIGHT
UNDER THE SKIN.
>> Rachael: IS SO MUCH FLAVOR.
>> Anne: A LITTLE CRUSHED RED
PEPPER IN THERE.
THIS IS ALWAYS KIND OF FUN, IT'S
A LITTLE BIT LIKE A SCIENCE
PROJECT.
WE KIND OF JUST WIGGLE OUR
FINGERS UNDER THE SKIN.
>> Rachael: IT'S ACTUALLY FUN!
[LAUGHTER]
IT LOOKS WEIRD, BUT --
THAT REMINDS ME OF THE PETER
GABRIEL VIDEO WITH THE DANCING
CHICKEN.
THAT WAS AWESOME.
>> Anne: WE JUST TAKE THIS YOU
MAY PASTE UNDER THE SKIN, JUST
WIGGLE IT AWAY FROM THE BREAST.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
IT KEEPS THE BREAST REALLY NICE
AND MOIST, AND THEN IT PERFUMES
THAT WITH ALL THIS
DELICIOUSNESS.
THEN THE OTHER THING ABOUT A
ROASTED CHICKEN WHICH IS REALLY
IMPORTANT TO DO IS TO TRUST IT.
IT'S AMAZING HOW A PIECE OF
STRING WILL CHANGE YOUR LIFE IN
TERMS OF CHICKEN.
I LIKE TO DO A NICE EASY TRUSS,
UNDERNEATH THE LEGS.
IT'S LIKE, "HANDS UP, HEADS UP!"
[LAUGHTER]
THEN YOU MAKE A X.
DROP IT DOWNTOWN, STRAIGHT
FORWARD.
POLICE TIGHT LIKE A LITTLE
CHICKEN HANDCUFF.
AND THEN RIGHT AROUND THE PACK,
YOU CAN TIDE UP LIKE A BOW.
THE REASON WE DO THIS, AND WHY
TRUSSING IS IMPORTANT IS
BECAUSE -- WELL, THERE'S A FEW
REASONS.
ONE, IT KEEPS THAT NICE
BEAUTIFUL FOOTBALL SHAPE.
LIKE THAT.
THEN WHAT IT DOES IS IT PULLS
THE LEGS UP TO PROTECT THE
BREAST.
THE BREAST COOKS FASTER AND HAS
LESS FAT THAN THE THIGHS AND THE
LEGS, SO THIS SPEEDS UP THE
COOKING TIME HERE AND SLOWS DOWN
THE COOKING TIME HERE.
>> Rachael: OH!
[APPLAUSE]
SO WE'VE GOT A BUNCH OF ONION,
CELERY, AND CARROTS.
YOUR BASIC FLAVOR PROFILE, YOUR
HARDWORKING STAFF.
WE HAVE A BUNDLE, WE HAVE BAY
LEAVES, AND WE'RE JUST GOING TO
PLUNK THESE GUYS.
WE GIVE THEM ANOTHER --
[LAUGHTER]
AT THE END ANOTHER BIT OF
LUBRICATION.
AND SOME SALT.
THEN WE TOSS THESE GUYS IN THE
OVEN.
THANK YOU, DOLL!
I'M GOING TO WASH MY HANDS.
WE WILL TOSS THEM IN A REALLY
HOT OVEN.
[LAUGHTER]
WE SERVE THOSE GUYS IN A REALLY
HOT OVEN FOR ABOUT 15 MINUTES.
THEY GET REALLY NICE AND BROWN
UP TOP.
450, 15 MINUTES, AND THEN RE-PUT
IT DOWN TO 375 FOR ANOTHER
45-ISH MINUTES.
THROUGH THE MAGIC OF TV --
HELLO, BEAUTIFUL BIRD!
[APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU.
LOOK AT THAT.
>> Rachael: LOVELY.
>> Rachael: GORGEOSO!
>> Anne: IS REALLY IMPORTANT
TO LET THE MESS.
WAS IN A CHICKEN IS MOISTURE.
TRYING TO GET OUT, DOING THE
MOISTURE.
LET ME OUT, LET ME OUT!
AND THEN WE DON'T KNOW.
THE CHICKEN JUICES DON'T KNOW
THAT THEY HAVE COME OUT OF THE
OVEN RIGHT AWAY.
WE LET THEM REST, AND THEY ARE
LIKE, "OH, WAIT A MINUTE!
WE CAN HANG IT RIGHT HERE!"
AND WHEN YOU CUT THE CHICKENS
ALL THE JUICES STAY IN THERE.
IF YOU CUT THEM RIGHT AWAY, THEY
WILL RUN OUT ALL OVER AND YOU
WILL BE LEFT WITH A SAD, DRY
CHICKEN.
[APPLAUSE]
SO THEN WHILE THE CHICKEN IS
RESTING WE WILL MAKE A LITTLE
JUS FOR THIS.
>> Rachael: TURNED ON THE
HEAT?
>> Anne: I WILL JUST TALK.
I LIKE THIS SET UP.
WE HAVE OUR CARROTS, ONION, AND
CELERY.
IT'S BEEN ROASTED WITH A LIST
CHICKEN JUICES AND SOME WINES
AND HERBS AND STUFF IN THE
BOTTOM.
I JUST LIKE TO ADD SOME NICE
BROWN CHICKEN STOCK TO THAT.
KIND OF GET IT TO THICKEN UP.
AND IT'S JUST SORT OF A JUS,
WITH THOSE CHUNKY VEGETABLES.
>> Rachael: SPOON IT RIGHT
OVER THE TOP.
>> Anne: WE LET THAT BE TO
BECOME RTS.
BRING TO BOIL, REDUCE TO A
SIMMER.
AND AT THAT TIME WE WILL WHIP TO
GIVE US A MASHED POTATOES.
>> Rachael: THESE ARE AMAZING
MASHED POTATOES!
>> Anne: I HAVE UCONN GOLD
POTATOES.
THEY ARE VERY THIN-SKINNED.
I DON'T EVEN PEEL THEM.
LOOK AT THAT, I THREW A FEW
CLOVES OF GARLIC RIGHT IN THE
WATER.
SO THAT THEY ARE GARLIC MASHED
POTATOES.
I HAVE HOT CREAM THAT I BOILED
OVER.
I HAVE COLD BUTTER, AND THEN WE
JUST WITH THEM TOGETHER.
AND THAT'S IT.
WE TASTE THEM FOR SALT, THE
WATER IS REALLY NICE AND SALTY.
[APPLAUSE]
THESE MIXERS ARE OLD SCHOOL BUT
I LOVE THEM.
I HAVE A NEW APPRECIATION.
>> Rachael: LOOK, I'VE GOT
SOME!
>> Anne: BEAUTIFUL.
ALL RIGHT, THERE WE GO.
DONESKI.
[APPLAUSE]
WINNER, WINTER, CHICKEN DINNER
RIGHT HERE!
IT MAKES ME SO HAPPY!
>> Rachael: CHICKEN AND MASHED
POTATOES -- IS THERE A MORE
UNIVERSAL "GOTTA LOVE THAT" KIND
OF A MEAL?
>> Anne: IT'S JUICY,
DELICIOUS, IT'S HERBY, AND A
LITTLE BIT FANCY BUT NOT REALLY.
IT'S RUSTIC BUT IT IS SO SOUL
SATISFYING.
>> Rachael: I'M GOING TO WORK
ON MY SOUL.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Anne: I LOVE THAT.
YOU KNOW WHY?
I'M GOING TO WORK ON MY SOUL AND
MY POTATOES COME TOO.
>> Rachael: OH, YES!
THAT'S RIDICULOUS!
[APPLAUSE]
HEY, ANNE?
THIS IS THE BIT WHERE YOU COME
BACK AGAIN SOON AND SHOW
EVERYBODY END OF A MEAL AT EVERY
BUDDY SHOULD KNOW HOW TO MAKE.
>> Anne: ABSOLUTELY!
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: BE SURE TO CATCH
AND ON HER SHOW, "WORST COOKS IN
AMERICA."
OF COURSE IT'S ON FOOD NETWORK.
SHE WILL BE BACK HERE SOON.
COMING UP NEXT, TIM TEBOW!
RIGHT AFTER THIS.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Rachael: ALL RIGHT!
[APPLAUSE]
MY NEXT GUEST IS TRULY A
>> Rachael: ALL RIGHT!
RENAISSANCE MAN.
MY NEXT GUEST IS TRULY A
HE IS AN NCAA NATIONAL CHAMPION,
RENAISSANCE MAN.
AND ON THE FELLOW QUARTERBACK, A
HE IS AN NCAA NATIONAL CHAMPION,
BASEBALL PLAYER, A
AND ON THE FELLOW QUARTERBACK, A
"NEW YORK TIMES" BEST-SELLING
BASEBALL PLAYER, A
AUTHOR, AND HE IS NOW A
"NEW YORK TIMES" BEST-SELLING
FILMMAKER, TOO!
AUTHOR, AND HE IS NOW A
WHAT A SHOW OFF!
FILMMAKER, TOO!
HE'S GOT QUITE THE RESUME AND
WHAT A SHOW OFF!
HE'S A LOVELY PERSON.
HE'S GOT QUITE THE RESUME AND
PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO HER SHOW,
HE'S A LOVELY PERSON.
OUR FRIEND TIM TEBOW.
PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO HER SHOW,
♪ ♪
OUR FRIEND TIM TEBOW.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Tim: THANK YOU!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
CONGRATULATIONS, THAT'S AMAZING!
>> Tim: THANK YOU!
>> Rachael: SHE IS AS FIT AS
CONGRATULATIONS, THAT'S AMAZING!
YOU.
>> Rachael: SHE IS AS FIT AS
HE WAS ASKING HOW ISABOO IS.
YOU.
HERE'S BIG PERSONAL NEWS FOR
HE WAS ASKING HOW ISABOO IS.
TIM.
HERE'S BIG PERSONAL NEWS FOR
HE JUST GOT ENGAGED!
TIM.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
HE JUST GOT ENGAGED!
>> Tim: THANK YOU.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: ISN'T THAT LOVELY?
>> Tim: THANK YOU.
>> Tim: IT IS.
>> Rachael: ISN'T THAT LOVELY?
>> Rachael: THAT'S ADORABLE!
>> Tim: IT IS.
WAS THAT THE ACTUAL MOMENT?
>> Rachael: THAT'S ADORABLE!
WHO WAS TAKING THE PICTURE?
WAS THAT THE ACTUAL MOMENT?
>> Tim: I HAD HIDDEN CMERAS
WHO WAS TAKING THE PICTURE?
EVERYWHERE.
>> Tim: I HAD HIDDEN CMERAS
THERE WERE A FEW THINGS I HAD TO
EVERYWHERE.
HAVE DONE.
THERE WERE A FEW THINGS I HAD TO
BEFORE SHE GOT ENGAGED SHE HAD
HAVE DONE.
TO HAVE HER NAILS DONE, SO MY
BEFORE SHE GOT ENGAGED SHE HAD
SISTER SECRETLY TOOK HER OUT AND
TO HAVE HER NAILS DONE, SO MY
THEY MADE IT ACT LIKE A
SISTER SECRETLY TOOK HER OUT AND
CHRISTMAS THING.
THEY MADE IT ACT LIKE A
I HAD VIDEO OF THE WHOLE THING.
CHRISTMAS THING.
>> Rachael: HOW DID IT TAKE
I HAD VIDEO OF THE WHOLE THING.
FOR YOU TO WRITE THE SPEECH?
>> Rachael: HOW DID IT TAKE
DID SHE KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT IT?
FOR YOU TO WRITE THE SPEECH?
DID SHE PICK UP THE RING OR DID
DID SHE KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT IT?
YOU?
DID SHE PICK UP THE RING OR DID
I WANT TO KNOW EVERYTHING!
YOU?
[LAUGHTER]
I WANT TO KNOW EVERYTHING!
WAS IT A SURPRISE?
[LAUGHTER]
>> Tim: IT WAS ABSOLUTELY A
WAS IT A SURPRISE?
SURPRISE.
>> Tim: IT WAS ABSOLUTELY A
THE PROBLEM WITH KEEPING A
SURPRISE.
SURPRISES YOU HAVE TO LIE A LOT!
THE PROBLEM WITH KEEPING A
I DID NOT LIKE IT!
SURPRISES YOU HAVE TO LIE A LOT!
BUT WE HAD SO MANY SURPRISES.
I DID NOT LIKE IT!
I HAD SET IT ALL UP.
BUT WE HAD SO MANY SURPRISES.
IT'S GOING TO BE A BIG CHRISTMAS
I HAD SET IT ALL UP.
DINNER WITH MOM AND DAD AT OUR
IT'S GOING TO BE A BIG CHRISTMAS
HOUSE, WITH ALL MY SIBLINGS AND
DINNER WITH MOM AND DAD AT OUR
EVERYTHING.
HOUSE, WITH ALL MY SIBLINGS AND
BUILDING UP LIKE IT'S REALLY
EVERYTHING.
NICE, WHERE A NICE DRESS,
BUILDING UP LIKE IT'S REALLY
EVERYTHING LIKE THAT.
NICE, WHERE A NICE DRESS,
BUT WE DON'T REALLY DRESS UP.
EVERYTHING LIKE THAT.
BUT WE DID IT FOR THAT.
BUT WE DON'T REALLY DRESS UP.
WE GO OUT THERE, I HAVE ALL THIS
BUT WE DID IT FOR THAT.
BUILD.
WE GO OUT THERE, I HAVE ALL THIS
I TAKE HER OUT THERE.
BUILD.
>> Rachael: YOU HAD THAT WHOLE
I TAKE HER OUT THERE.
SET BUILDS?
>> Rachael: YOU HAD THAT WHOLE
>> Tim: ALL OF IT BUILT JUST
SET BUILDS?
FOR THAT.
>> Tim: ALL OF IT BUILT JUST
I HAD AN OLD WOODEN BENCH AND
FOR THAT.
FULL SILVER AND HAD THE DB MET
I HAD AN OLD WOODEN BENCH AND
AND
FULL SILVER AND HAD THE DB MET
AND A FEW OTHER PERSONAL THINGS
AND
ON THERE.
AND A FEW OTHER PERSONAL THINGS
>> Rachael: HE BUILT A BENCH!
ON THERE.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Rachael: HE BUILT A BENCH!
JOHN THROUGH A BOX IN MY HEAD!
[LAUGHTER]
>> Tim: BUT THE BEST PART -- I
GET DOWN, I PROPOSE.
WE HAD A SONG CALLED "THE
WEDDING SONG."
HE'S FROM SOUTH AFRICA, SO IS
SHE.
I PLAYED IT ON MY PHONE.
WE START TO DANCE.
HE COMES OUT BEHIND THE HEY BALE
AND STARTED SINGING IT.
[AUDIENCE REACTS]
SHE WAS BLOWN AWAY.
WE ARE DANCING, I'M HOLDING A
PRETTY TIGHT, I GIVE A SIGNAL.
THEN HER PARENTS COME OUT AND
SHE HAS TWO SETS OF PARENTS OF
THEIR STANDING BEHIND HER.
I HAVE ANOTHER SURPRISE, I
TURNED AROUND, SHE STARTS
CRYING.
SHE DIDN'T KNOW THEY WERE IN THE
COUNTRY FROM SOUTH AFRICA.
THEN WE DID THE SAME THING WITH
HER BEST FRIENDS.
>> Rachael: ARE YOU FOR REAL?
YOU ARE A SUPERHERO!
[APPLAUSE]
THE FIVE MEN IN OUR AUDIENCE
TODAY ARE GOING TO GO CRYING OUT
THE DOOR, SOBBING FOR LIFE
BECAUSE THEIR WIVES AND
GIRLFRIENDS WILL NEVER FORGIVE
THEM FOR NOT BEING TIM TEBOW!
[LAUGHTER]
THAT IS BEAUTIFUL.
HOW LONG DID IT TAKE HER TO SAY
YES?
>> Rachael: SHE SAID IT REALLY
QUICKLY.
AND I WAS LIKE, "PERFECT!
ALL RIGHT!"
>> Rachael: THIS TIME OF THE
YEAR'S PROM SEASON, BUT TIM CAN
SPEAK WITH HIS WHOLE HEART AS
WELL AS HE CAN COME HIS
BEAUTIFUL BRIDE TO BE.
THIS TIME OF THE YEAR'S PROM
SEASON BUT THEY ARE VERY SPECIAL
PROBLEMS.
CAN YOU EXPLAIN?
>> Tim: YEAH, THIS PAST
WEEKEND WE HAVE WHAT IS CALLED
"NIGHT TO SHINE."
IT'S A WORLDWIDE PROM FOR PEOPLE
WITH SPECIAL NEEDS.
IN 24 COUNTRIES, ALL 50 STATES,
AND 655 LOCATIONS, WE HAD A
WORLDWIDE PROBLEM FOR PEOPLE
WITH SPECIAL NEEDS.
OVER 200,000 VOLUNTEERS AND OVER
100,000 PEOPLE WITH SPECIAL
NEEDS WERE CROWNED AS THE KING
OR QUEEN OF THE PROBLEM.
IT'S TRULY MY FAVORITE NIGHT OF
THE YEAR.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: I KNOW!
HE LITERALLY SHOULD HAVE A CAPE,
RIGHT?
HE'S JUST A REAL-LIFE SUPERHERO.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
YOU'RE ALSO THE HOST OF A NEW
CBS SHOW THAT IS PRODUCED BY
LeBRON JAMES.
IT'S CALLED "MILLION DOLLAR
MILE."
SEE IF I'VE GOT THIS RIGHT.
ATHLETES ARE COME PEELING AND I
ASSUME
A MILE-LONG OBSTACLE COURSE?
AND THEY COULD WIN $1 MILLION?
IS THAT THE DEAL?
>> Tim: IF YOU GET THROUGH IT
CAN BE WHEN A MILLION DOLLARS.
THE PROBLEM IS THERE'S ANOTHER
ATHLETE THAT MIGHT BE A LITTLE
BIT BETTER, AND HE IS CHASING
YOU
YOU GET A TWO MINUTE HEAD START.
IT'S THE CRAZIEST OBSTACLE
COURSE YOU'VE EVER SEEN.
>> Rachael: DID YOU GO THROUGH
IT?
>> Tim: I DIDN'T GO ALL OF IT,
BUT I HAVE TO BE HONEST -- I DID
JUMP OFF A 15 STORY BUILDING TO
INTROIT.
IT'S INSANE.
THE OBSTACLE COURSE IS INSANE.
I HEARD ALL ABOUT IT IN PREPPING
FOR THE SHOW, BUT WHEN I SHOWED
UP I WAS LIKE, "ARE YOU KIDDING
ME?"
>> Rachael: SO THIS IS NOT
EASY.
>> Tim: IT'S INSANE.
IT'S REALLY COOL, THOUGH, AND
REALLY FUN.
>> Rachael: DON'T YOU WANT TO
RUN THE WHOLE THING JUST TO SEE
IF YOU DID?
>> Tim: OF COURSE, BUT I WAS
ALSO TRAINING FOR BASEBALL!
>> Rachael: WELL, THERE IS
THAT!
[LAUGHS]
HE DID THIS WITH YOUR BROTHER,?-
RIGHT?
A FAMILY PROJECT?
>> Tim: SIX YEARS AGO I READ A
SCRIPT.
>> Rachael: WHAT'S THE NAME?
>> Tim: "RUN THE RACE."
>> Rachael: AND IT'S NOT
SCREAMING, IT'S A THEATER THING.
"RUN THE RACE."
>> Tim: I SHOWED IT TO SOME
FRIENDS AND FAMILY, THEY CRIED.
IT MOVED US.
I EVEN TOOK A TRIP AND I TOOK IT
WITH ME IN THE PHILIPPINES.
TO SEE IF IT MOVES ME AGAIN, I
READ IT AGAIN.
A TOTAL IMPACTED ME.
I WAS LIKE IT, "LET'S TELL THE
STORY."
I NEVER HAD THE GOAL OF GETTING
IN THE MOVIE INDUSTRY.
I LIKE TELLING STORIES AND I
LIKE ENCOURAGING PEOPLE.
THIS MOVIE TELLS A STORY OF TWO
BROTHERS, THEIR MOM PASSES AWAY
AND THEIR DAD IS AN ALCOHOLIC.
THEY ARE FIGHTING TO SUPPORT
EACH OTHER, TO GET THROUGH LIFE
AND TO MAKE IT.
STORIES ABOUT BELIEF AND HOPE
AND LOVE AND LOYALTY AND
SUPPORTING ONE ANOTHER.
HOW ON ANY SPEAKS TO THE LEFT, A
COACH, A PASTOR, SO MANY OF THE
PEOPLE.
>> Rachael: IS THIS DURING THE
MAKING OF IT?
OH, WOW.
>> Tim: IS ABOUT SPORTS,
RELATIONSHIPS, SIGNIFICANT
OTHERS.
IT'S A STORY ABOUT LOYALTY AND
BEING ABLE TO HAVE EACH OTHER'S
BACK.
I WANTED TO MAKE THIS BECAUSE I
WANTED TO HAVE A REAL LIFE-TYPE
MOVIE, BUT AT THE SAME TIME BE
ENCOURAGING FOR YOUNG PEOPLE.
>> Rachael: THIS IS HOW YOU
LIVE YOUR OWN LIFE.
IT'S FAMILIAR GROUND FOR YOU.
>> Tim: THAT PEOPLE CAN WALK
AWAY KNOWING THAT LIFE WILL
ALWAYS BE EASY AND PERFECT, BUT
I CAN WALK WITH FAITH, HOPE, AND
LOVE READY TO TAKE ON THE
OBSTACLES THROWN AT ME.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT TO SAY AFTER THAT.
TIM, I WISH YOU EVERYTHING
BEAUTIFUL IN LIFE.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THANK YOU SO MUCH OF OUR DEAR
FRIEND, TIM.
CONGRATULATIONS TO YOU AND YOUR
BRIDE.
YOU SHOULD BRING HERE DON MY CAR
HERE NEXT TIME.
I HONEYMOONED IN SOUTH AFRICA, I
CAN MAKE SOME REALLY GOOD
SOUTH AFRICAN FRUIT!
I LOVE SOUTH AFRICAN CUISINE.
HAPPY TO COOK SOME FOR HER NEXT
TIME YOU COME.
HIS MOVIE, "RUN THE RACE," IS IN
THEATERS NEXT FRIDAY.
WHAT A WONDERFUL THING TO DO
WITH YOUR FAMILY FOR THE
WEEKEND.
TAKE A LOOK AT A CLIP BEFORE WE
GO TO BREAK.
AGAIN, GIVE IT UP FOR TIM TEBOW.
[APPLAUSE]
WHAT A STORY!
>> I HEARD YOU'RE GETTING REAL
WELL INTO BALL CLUB THE SEASON.
SPEAKER DID YOU?
>> THE WORD IS THAT YOU'RE GOING
TO SHATTER MY DISTRICT RECORDS.
>> I WILL WIPE YOUR NAME OFF THE
RECORD BOOKS.
YOU CAN COUNT ON THAT.
>> WE ARE FAMILY.
>> YOU THINK THAT SUPPOSED TO
MEAN SOMETHING?
>> IT MEANS EVERYTHING.
>> MEANS NOTHING.
WE ARE FAMILY.
YOU ARE SOMEONE WHO LOVED US
AFTER A MOM DIED.
LET'S GO
Stronger is blasting
her tumors...
without risking her bones.
It's training her
good cells...
to fight the bad guys.
Stronger is less pain...
new hope...
more fight.
It's doing everything
in your power...
and everything in ours.
Stronger, is changing even
faster than they do.
Because we don't just want
your kids to grow up.
We want them to
grow up stronger.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: HEY, GUYS!
TODAY WE ARE GOING TO DO A MAKE
YOUR OWN TAKE-OUT MEAL.
WHEN I'M IN THE CITY, OF COURSE
I CAN GET ANY CUISINE FROM ALL
OVER EARTH FLEW TO HER APARTMENT
USUALLY IN LESS THAN AN HOUR.
BUT WHEN I'M UP IN THE COUNTRY,
WE DON'T HAVE ANY DELIVERY OF
TAKE-OUT FOOD.
BUT TODAY I'M GOING TO MAKE A
TAIWANESE STYLE SUFFERED.
SUPER DELICIOUS, SUPER EASY, SO
FLAVORFUL, AND IT WOULD BE
REALLY FUN TO ENTERTAIN WITH
THIS MEAL.
IT COOKS IT PRETTY QUICKLY.
I WILL START WITH SHRIMP TOAST,
WHAT OF MY ALL-TIME FAVORITES.
I'VE GOT A LOT OF GINGER.
ABOUT AN INCH OR AN INCH AND
HALF OF GINGER ROOT, WHICH I'M
ADDING DOWN TO HALF A POUND OF
SHRIMP.
PEELED AND DEVEINED, OF COURSE.
THIS IS FOR SIX TOASTS THAT WE
CUT IN HALF, SO YOU WILL END UP
WITH 12 PIECES OF SHRIMP TOAST.
THAT WOULD BE ENOUGH FOR UP TO
FOUR ADULTS.
TO THAT I'M GOING TO ADD FOUR
SCALLIONS, COARSELY CHOPPED.
A FAT CLUBE OF GARLIC.
A SMALL HANDFUL OF CILANTRO.
A DRIZZLE OF TOASTED SESAME OIL.
AND SOME SOY SAUCE.
A DRIZZLE OF EACH.
THE SOY SAUCE IS YOUR NATURAL
SALT.
2 TEASPOONS COME ABOUT
2 TEASPOONS, OF CORNSTARCH.
A LITTLE WHITE PEPPER.
AND THEN IN A DISH WE ARE GOING
TO CROSS TO HALF OF THE TOAST.
WE'VE GOT SIX PIECES OF WHITE
SLICING BREAD.
WE'LL CUT THOSE CORNER TO CORNER
AFTER THEY ARE COATED WITH THE
SHRIMP AND THE SESAME SEED.
THEN WHEN YOU PLATE IT, EVERY
OTHER TOAST HAS THIS COATING OF
TOASTED SESAME SEED ON IT.
IT'S DELICIOUS.
AND ONE EGG WHITE ALSO GOES IN
HERE.
IT HELPS KEEP ANYBODY TOGETHER.
IT HELPS THEM ALL GET ALONG AND
SAY STUCK TO THE TOAST.
IN MY PAN, BETWEEN MEDIUM AND
MEDIUM-HIGH, IT'S ABOUT A
QUARTER TO HALF AN INCH OF OIL.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DEEP FRIDAYS.
WE WILL SHALLOW FRY THEM.
I'VE GOT A HEATING UP BETWEEN
MEDIUM AND MEDIUM-HIGH.
I'VE GOT A TRANSFER TRAY.
SO WHEN WE ARE DONE COOKING THE
FIRST BATCH THEY CAN DRAIN OVER
HERE.
OKAY?
WE'RE GOING TO ZIP THESE GUYS
TOGETHER INTO A SICK PASTE.
THAT LOOKS GOOD.
THEN WE ARE GOING TO TAKE A
SMALL SPATULA.
I WILL SHOW YOU ONE HERE.
COAT THE WHITE BREAD WITH THE
SHRIMP PASTE.
JUST LIKE THIS.
A NICE EVEN LATER.
YOU CAN MOUNT IT UP A LITTLE BI
BIT.
AND THEN WITH HALF OF THEM,
PRESS THEM GENTLY.
GET AN EVEN COATING INTO THE
TOASTED SESAME JUST LIKE THAT.
THEN WHEN WE CUT THEM YOU ARE
GOING TO CUT THEM CORNER TO
CORNER.
JUST LIKE THIS.
WHEN THEY ARE ALL TOGETHER, COOK
HALF AT A TIME IN THE OIL.
WE HAVE SOME WORK IN THE
KITCHEN.
I WILL SHOW YOU WHAT THAT LOOKS
LIKE.
THIS IS JUST THE FIRST COURSE.
GUESS WHAT WE ARE MAKING?
WE WILL MAKE A TAIWANESE STYLE
MEAT SAUCE THAT YOU CAN MAKE
WITH PORK WILL BE FREE OF A
CHICKEN IF YOU'D LIKE.
I'VE PUT COOKING HERE.
INSTEAD OF OVER SPAGHETTI, IT'LL
BE OVER CHINESE EGG THE BE LIKE
A SPAGHETTI MEAT SAUCE DINNER
BUT TAIWANESE STYLE.
AFTER THIS.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
WW Freestyle
is for everbody
who wants to eat the
foods they love
and still lose weight.
It's proven to help
people lose weight,
and feel happier.
Join now at ww.com for
$0 Dollars
and get your first month free
Offer ends February 25th.
New Whole Blends Ginger
Recovery.
Blended with purpose, for
fragile hair.
With revitalizing ginger, known
to recover strength,
and golden honey.
As a whole blend,
it provides twice the breakage
protection.
To make hair stronger instantly.
Blended makes us better.
Whole Blends.
By Garnier, naturally.
I had this chest cold, but my
medicine kept wearing off.
(coughs)
Ah!
I missed you!
Then I discovered Mucinex.
One pill lasts 12 hours,
and I'm good.
Mucinex releases fast
and lasts 12 hours, not 4.
Let's End This.
♪ I'M A BIG KID NOW ♪
♪ WENT FROM BABY BOTTLES TO
DRINKING FROM SIPPY CUPS ♪
♪ WENT FROM WEARING DIAPERS TO
ROCKING THESE FRESH PULL-UPS ♪
♪ WE'RE 50 MILLION STRONG ♪
♪ SO PUT ON YOUR PULL-UPS
AND HELP US SING THIS SONG ♪
♪ WE'RE 50 MILLION STRONG ♪
When you eat a bowl
of oatmeal,
you're getting beta-glucan.
That's a soluble fiber
that slows the breakdown
of carbohydrates.
And that provides energy
that lasts.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: FOR THE MEAT SAUCE
AND PASTA, KIND OF LIKE
TAIWANESE SPAGHETTI AND MEAT
SAUCE, WE ARE GOING TO START BY
BROWNING MUSHROOMS FIRST.
ABOUT HALF A POUND.
I USED MAITAKE OR HEN OF THE
WOODS.
WHAT I LIKE ABOUT THIS MUSHROOMS
YOU CAN PULL IT APART, HE DON'T
HAVE A CHOP THEM.
OF COURSE YOU CAN USE SHIITAKE
OR CHOP UP SOME CARMINE
MUSHROOMS.
IT'S A NICE BEEFY FLAVOR
THESE ARE GOOD AND THE HIGH TEMP
OF INCOME IS LOW.
WE HAVE OUR SHRIMP TOAST.
I TOOK STORE ABOUT SWEET CHILI
SAUCE AND PUT THAT ALONG SIDE.
THAT'S OUR APPETIZER FOR THIS
DISH.
TO THE BROWN MUSHROOMS, LET THEM
BROWN FIRST BEFORE YOU EVER SALT
THEM.
THEY GET MEATY AND DARK AND MORE
MUSHROOM GOODNESS FLAVOR WILL
COME OUT OF THEM.
IF YOU DON'T SOLVE THEM
IMMEDIATELY.
SALT DRAWS OUT THE LIQUID IN IT
SLOWS DOWN THE BROWNING PROCESS
OF THE MUSHROOM.
TWO OF THE ONES WE BROWN FIRST
AT A LITTLE BIT OF HIGH
TEMPERATURE COOKING OIL OVER
MEDIUM-HIGH TO HIGH HEAT I THEN
ADD A POUND OF GROUND PORK.
OR YOU CAN SUBSTITUTE, AS I SAID
SAID, GROUND BEEF OR EVEN GROUND
CHICKEN.
NOW WE ARE READY TO ADD SALT BUT
WERE NOT GOING TO ADD KOSHER
SALT.
WE ARE GOING TO USE SOY SAUCE.
WE'RE GOING TO USE A COMBINATION
OF DARK SOY SAUCE, WHICH IS A
LITTLE THICKER AND SWEETER.
A COUPLE TEASPOONS OF THAT.
LIGHT SOY SAUCE, WHICH HAS A
HIGHER SALT CONTENT BUT IS
THINNER.
YOU CAN SEE THROUGH IT A LITTLE
BIT.
IT'S MORE TRANSLUCENT.
IT'S ACTUALLY A LITTLE SALTIER
THAN THE DARK SOY SAUCE.
THAT'S A LITTLE SWEETER.
THEY WILL PUT A SPRINKLE OF
LIGHT BROWN SUGAR.
THEY LOVE -- TAIWANESE COOKING
ELECTS A LITTLE BIT OF SUGAR TO
BALANCE HEAT AND SALT.
WE ARE GOING TO STIR THAT
ALTOGETHER.
START A
NICE, CINNAMON, FIVE SPICE
POWDER AND SO MUCH FLAVOR AND SO
LITTLE AMOUNT.
1 TEASPOON OF THIS AND THE
FLAVOR WILL PERMEATE THIS DISH
IMMEDIATELY.
IT'LL BE SO FREQUENT AND
DELICIOUS.
THAT'S ABOUT A THIRD OF A PALM
FULL.
I MEASURED RIGHT IN THE PALM OF
MY HAND.
IF A LITTLE TOO MUCH COMES OUT
YOU CAN PUT IT BACK IN THE JAR.
WRITE DOWN INTO THE DISH.
TO MAKE THIS NICE AND SAUCY ARE
GOING TO ADD A LITTLE STOCK OR
BONE BROTH.
CHICKEN OR PORK OR BEEF STOCK,
IF YOU'RE USING BEEF OF COURSE.
WE ARE GOING TO SPRINKLE IN
THESE GUYS.
YOU CAN ORDER THEM AND   ONLINET
THEM IN THE ASIAN MARKETS.
IF YOU HAVE A SPECIALTY STORE IN
YOUR COMMUNITY THAT SELLS ASIAN
FOOD.
THESE ARE FRIED SHALLOTS.
DELICIOUS.
I TRY TO ONLY BUY THEM EVERY
MONTH OR SO BECAUSE THEY TEND TO
EAT THE ENTIRE BAG IF I COOK
WITH THEM.
THEY ARE DELICIOUS SPECKLED ON
SALAD OF ANY TYPE, ANY NIGHT OF
THE WEEK.
IF YOU CAN'T FIND FRIED
SHALLOTS, THEY ARE LIKE THE
FIGHT AND NEEDS IN THE GROCERY
STORE.
THAT'S WHEN TWO SLICKS.
IF YOU CAN'T FIND THEM AND YOU
DON'T WANT TO GO THROUGH THE
BOTHER OF ORDERING THEM ONLINE,
JUST ORDER A FINE SHALL
IT.
IT'LL STILL GIVE IT A SHOT
FLAVOR.
A LOT OF THE FLAVOR COMES FROM
THIS.
THIS IS A CHINESE STYLE SHERRY
OR COOKING LINE.
THIS IS RICE WINE.
IF HE CAN'T FIND THIS, AGAIN,
YOU CAN ORDER IT ONLINE OR GIVE
THAT A LOT OF THE LARGER SPIRIT
STORES HERE IN NEW YORK.
WINE AND LIQUOR STORES.
IF YOU CAN'T FIND THIS, JUST USE
DRY COOKING SHERRY.
IT'S DELICIOUS.
YOU GIVE US THE SAUCE A
PARTICULAR FLAVOR.
IT'S FABULOUS.
WE WILL STIR THIS TOGETHER AND
DROP AT A CHINESE NOODLES.
YOU COULD SERVE IT WITH
SPAGHETTI, IT'S DELICIOUS.
IF YOUR STORE HAS A LARGE ASIAN
FOODS AISLE YOU CAN BUY CHINESE
EGG NOODLES.
IT'LL BE LIKE EGG SPAGHETTI.
IT IS SUPER QUICK COOKING, OF
COURSE.
WHEN WE COME BACK WE WILL TOSS
US TO AND SERVE IT.
Pageantry. Poise.
Welcome to the dog show
where humans compete
for the ultimate prize.
Avocados from Mexico.
They're healthy,
delicious on everything
and always in season.
Looks like the dogs
have settled in.
They can almost
sniff the bum of victory.
That's a good sit.
A shake.
And...
[dog bark]
...a stay!
Amazing form.
I'm sure he's making
someone very proud right now.
Oh, we've got a runner.
[dog whines]
Ah, the guac got to her.
That will land you
in the penalty cone.
[splat]
♪ Avocados from Mexico ♪
Just between us, cleaning with a
mop and bucket is such a hassle.
Well I switched to Swiffer Wet
Jet and it's awesome.
It's an all-in-one that absorbs
dirt and grime deep inside.
And it helps prevent streaks and
haze.
Stop Cleaning. Start Swiffering
Man 1: This is my body of proof.
Woman 1:
Proof of less joint pain...
Woman 2:
...and clearer skin.
Woman 3:
This is my
body of proof.
Man 2:
Proof that I can fight
psoriatic arthritis...
Woman 4:
...with HUMIRA.
Woman 5:
HUMIRA targets
and blocks
a specific source
of inflammation
that contributes
to both joint and
skin symptoms.
It's proven
to help relieve pain,
stop further
irreversible joint damage,
and clear skin in many adults.
HUMIRA is the #1
prescribed biologic
for psoriatic arthritis.
AVO: HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections.
Serious and sometimes
fatal infections,
including tuberculosis,
and cancers, including
lymphoma, have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Woman 6:
Ask your rheumatologist
about HUMIRA.
Woman 7: Go to MyPsAProof.com
to see proof in action.
[phone ringing]
Remember the way we
used to do things?
Hey man...
Like connect with friends?
Dig it!
Or get in shape?
Or sell a house
and pay a real estate
agent a big commission.
[crash]
At Redfin, we charge
you a 1% listing fee.
And because Redfin.com is
America's #1 brokerage site
our agents get more
eyes on your home
so you sell for
thousands more
than the one next door.
Don't get stuck in the past.
Sell with a Redfin Agent.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
WHENEVER YOU ARE COOKING POTS OF
ANY KIND, THIS IS A QUICK
COOKING CHINESE EGG
NOODLE.
A LONG NOODLE MAKE OF EGGS, SO
IT COOKS VERY QUICKLY.
ALWAYS UNDER COOK BY ONE MENTOR
FROM THE COOK TIME ON THE
PACKAGE BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING TO
TOSS THE PASTA WITH SOMETHING
HOT.
IN THIS CASE, OUR TAIWANESE MEAT
SAUCE.
THAT'S GOING TO CARRY OVER THE
COOKING ACTION.
YOU DON'T WANT THE NOODLES OR
YOUR DRIED PASTAS OF ANY KIND TO
BE OVERCOOKED.
UNDER COOK, THAT IT WILL TASTE
JUST PERFECT.
THIS IS OUR TAIWANESE MEAT
SAUCE.
I KNOW, IT SMELLS INSANE!
I WISH YOU HAD SMELL-O-VISION.
[LAUGHTER]
OH, MY GOD, IT'S CRAZY!
THEY SMELL SO GOOD!
[APPLAUSE]
ALONG WITH OUR TAIWANESE STYLE
MEAT SAUCE THAT WE ARE GOING TO
PUT INTO OUR FAMILY-STYLE
POSSIBLE, WOW.
CRAZY!
ALONG WITH THAT WE HAVE SHRIMP
TOAST WITH A STORE-BOUGHT SWEET
CHILI SAUCE.
SHRIMP TOASTED SESAME SEEDS.
YES PLEASE!
THIS IS DELICIOUS.
NO EFFORT.
THE MEAT SAUCE THAT CAN BE
COOKED IN 15 OR 20 MINUTES.
YES!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
MAKE YOUR OWN TAKE-OUT!
DELICIOUS!
MY MOUTH WAS WATERING.
GRAB A SNACK AND COME RIGHT BAC
BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Rachael: IT IS SO RUDE TO
[APPLAUSE]
TALK WITH YOUR MOUTH FULL, BUT
>> Rachael: IT IS SO RUDE TO
THAT SHRIMP TOAST IS SO GOOD!
TALK WITH YOUR MOUTH FULL, BUT
[LAUGHTER]
THAT SHRIMP TOAST IS SO GOOD!
THANK YOU TO ALL OF MY GUESTS
[LAUGHTER]
TODAY.
THANK YOU TO ALL OF MY GUESTS
I WISH I HAD ANOTHER ONE.
TODAY.
ONE OF
I WISH I HAD ANOTHER ONE.
KELSEY GRAMMER'S BEERS.
ONE OF
THEY ARE AMAZING.
KELSEY GRAMMER'S BEERS.
WE MISS YOU, THANK YOU FOR
THEY ARE AMAZING.
COMING BACK.
WE MISS YOU, THANK YOU FOR
MY GIRLFRIEND ANNE BURRELL, THE
COMING BACK.
ADORABLE TIM TEBOW.
MY GIRLFRIEND ANNE BURRELL, THE
CONGRATULATIONS AGAIN ON YOUR
ADORABLE TIM TEBOW.
ENGAGEMENT.
CONGRATULATIONS AGAIN ON YOUR
WE WILL SEE WHEN WE SEE YOU,
ENGAGEMENT.
EVERYBODY.
WE WILL SEE WHEN WE SEE YOU,
BYE-BYE.
EVERYBODY.
[APPLAUSE]
BYE-BYE.
♪ ♪
♪ LET'S GO ♪
>> Announcer: YOUR ME TIME'S