♪ ♪
>> Announcer: TODAY ON
"RACHAEL RAY."
THIS DESERVING WIFE AND MOTHER
LOST 200 POUNDS.
NOW, GRETA IS MAKING HER OVER
JUST IN TIME FOR AN
UNFORGETTABLE WEDDING REDO.
THEN, LIGHTING UP YOUR KIDS
LUNCHES WITH THE LIVELY JENNY TO
JENNY MOLLEN.
>> AND IT MAKES YOU VERY
REGULAR.
[LAUGHS]
>> Announcer: PLUS SIT AND
STAY FOR THIS AMAZING WEIGHT
LOSS DOG.
AND, THIS FLAVORFUL THAI SHRIMP
AND CORN SOUP COULD BE WHAT'S
FOR DINNER TONIGHT.
>> Rachael: TRY IT, YOU'LL
LIKE IT.
[LAUGHTER]
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: ALL RIGHT, I AM
♪ ♪
HERE WITH MY DEAR FRIEND GRETTA
>> Rachael: ALL RIGHT, I AM
MONAHAN AND TODAY SHOW IS ABOUT
HERE WITH MY DEAR FRIEND GRETTA
BIG TRANSFORMATIONS.
MONAHAN AND TODAY SHOW IS ABOUT
CREDIT WAS ALL FOR BEING IN ON
BIG TRANSFORMATIONS.
THIS ONE.
CREDIT WAS ALL FOR BEING IN ON
WAS THIS LIKE -- >> Gretta: I
THIS ONE.
LOVED IT, MY FAVORITE.
WAS THIS LIKE -- >> Gretta: I
AN AMAZING STORY.
LOVED IT, MY FAVORITE.
>> Rachael: YOU GUYS, OUR
AN AMAZING STORY.
FIRST GUEST MADE A BIG
>> Rachael: YOU GUYS, OUR
TRANSITION.
FIRST GUEST MADE A BIG
I MEAN BIG.
TRANSITION.
SHE LOST LIKE TO GRETA'S.
I MEAN BIG.
SHE LOST 185 POUNDS.
SHE LOST LIKE TO GRETA'S.
>> Gretta: IT'S INCREDIBLE
SHE LOST 185 POUNDS.
WHAT SHE DID.
>> Gretta: IT'S INCREDIBLE
>> Rachael: SHE GOT MARRIED 14
WHAT SHE DID.
YEARS AGO, THERE'S A WEDDING
>> Rachael: SHE GOT MARRIED 14
PICTURE, GOD BLESS.
YEARS AGO, THERE'S A WEDDING
IT'S INCREDIBLE.
PICTURE, GOD BLESS.
NOW SHE WANTS TO SAY "I DO"
IT'S INCREDIBLE.
AGAIN IN HER DREAM DRESS!
NOW SHE WANTS TO SAY "I DO"
WE WILL HAVE TO GIVE THEM LIKE A
AGAIN IN HER DREAM DRESS!
BREAK TO BRUSH THEIR TEETH, IT'S
WE WILL HAVE TO GIVE THEM LIKE A
SO SWEET!
BREAK TO BRUSH THEIR TEETH, IT'S
>> Gretta: THEY WILL HAVE TO
SO SWEET!
HAVE HANKIES.
>> Gretta: THEY WILL HAVE TO
>> Rachael: TOOK UP THE STORY.
HAVE HANKIES.
SPEAK TO MY NAME IS VALERIE AND
>> Rachael: TOOK UP THE STORY.
I'M FROM HEWLETT, NEW YORK AND
SPEAK TO MY NAME IS VALERIE AND
I'VE LOST 185 POUNDS.
I'M FROM HEWLETT, NEW YORK AND
I'VE STRUGGLED WITH MY WEIGHT
I'VE LOST 185 POUNDS.
SINCE I WAS A LITTLE GIRL.
I'VE STRUGGLED WITH MY WEIGHT
THE HEAVIEST I WAS, WAS
SINCE I WAS A LITTLE GIRL.
354 POUNDS.
THE HEAVIEST I WAS, WAS
I WOULD WALK TWO BLOCKS AND MY
354 POUNDS.
KNEES WOULD HURT.
I WOULD WALK TWO BLOCKS AND MY
IT WAS DIFFICULT FOR ME TO SIT
KNEES WOULD HURT.
IN A MOVIE THEATER CHAIR.
IT WAS DIFFICULT FOR ME TO SIT
AND I WAS JUST ABOUT TO GET
IN A MOVIE THEATER CHAIR.
MARRIED AND I WAS FRIGHTENED
AND I WAS JUST ABOUT TO GET
BECAUSE I REALLY WANTED TO BE
MARRIED AND I WAS FRIGHTENED
HEALTHY FOR MY HUSBAND AND FOR
BECAUSE I REALLY WANTED TO BE
THE FAMILY WE WANTED TO START.
HEALTHY FOR MY HUSBAND AND FOR
>> THE DOCTORS TOLD HER THAT IF
THE FAMILY WE WANTED TO START.
SHE DIDN'T LOSE WEIGHT, IT WOULD
>> THE DOCTORS TOLD HER THAT IF
BE VERY DANGEROUS FOR HER.
SHE DIDN'T LOSE WEIGHT, IT WOULD
>> Valerie: I DECIDED TO HAVE
BE VERY DANGEROUS FOR HER.
WEIGHT LOSS SURGERY.
>> Valerie: I DECIDED TO HAVE
OVER THE YEARS I'VE BEEN ABLE TO
WEIGHT LOSS SURGERY.
KEEP THE WEIGHT OFF BECAUSE I AM
OVER THE YEARS I'VE BEEN ABLE TO
A MOTHER AND I'M CONSTANTLY
KEEP THE WEIGHT OFF BECAUSE I AM
MOVING.
A MOTHER AND I'M CONSTANTLY
>> I'M VERY PROUD OF MY WIFE FOR
MOVING.
DOING EVERYTHING SHE DID TO LOSE
>> I'M VERY PROUD OF MY WIFE FOR
THE WEIGHT.
DOING EVERYTHING SHE DID TO LOSE
>> Valerie: MICHAEL AND I HAVE
THE WEIGHT.
BEEN MARRIED FOR 14 YEARS NOW.
>> Valerie: MICHAEL AND I HAVE
IF THE IDEA OF REDOING MY
BEEN MARRIED FOR 14 YEARS NOW.
WEDDING IS THE PERSON I AM NOW
IF THE IDEA OF REDOING MY
IS TRULY EXCITING FOR ME.
WEDDING IS THE PERSON I AM NOW
AND NOW I HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY TO
IS TRULY EXCITING FOR ME.
START FRESH.
AND NOW I HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY TO
♪ ♪
START FRESH.
>> I'M HERE AT KLINEFELTER IN
♪ ♪
NEW YORK CITY WHICH IS A TREAT,
>> I'M HERE AT KLINEFELTER IN
THE BRIDAL MECCA IN THE WORLD.
NEW YORK CITY WHICH IS A TREAT,
WELCOME TO KLINEFELTER.
THE BRIDAL MECCA IN THE WORLD.
>> Valerie: THIS IS SO SUR
WELCOME TO KLINEFELTER.
SURREAL!
>> Valerie: THIS IS SO SUR
>> MEET VALERIE.
SURREAL!
>> LOOK AT YOU, CONGRATULATIONS!
>> MEET VALERIE.
>> Valerie: IT FEELS SO
>> LOOK AT YOU, CONGRATULATIONS!
AMAZING, I KNOW I'M GOING TO
>> Valerie: IT FEELS SO
FIND SOMETHING BEAUTIFUL.
AMAZING, I KNOW I'M GOING TO
I THINK THE DRESS I'M PICTURING
FIND SOMETHING BEAUTIFUL.
FOR MYSELF IS SOMETHING A LITTLE
I THINK THE DRESS I'M PICTURING
MORE CONSERVATIVE, SOMETHING
FOR MYSELF IS SOMETHING A LITTLE
WITH THE SLEEVE POSSIBLY BECAUSE
MORE CONSERVATIVE, SOMETHING
I'M SELF-CONSCIOUS ABOUT MY
WITH THE SLEEVE POSSIBLY BECAUSE
ARMS.
I'M SELF-CONSCIOUS ABOUT MY
>> IT'S REALLY BEAUTIFUL, REALLY
ARMS.
STUNNING.
>> IT'S REALLY BEAUTIFUL, REALLY
THAT'S CLASSY AND SASSY.
STUNNING.
I FEEL BEAUTIFUL.
THAT'S CLASSY AND SASSY.
I FEEL TINY.
I FEEL BEAUTIFUL.
WHICH I'VE NEVER FELT BEFORE IN
I FEEL TINY.
MY LIFE.
WHICH I'VE NEVER FELT BEFORE IN
I AM BEAUTIFUL.
MY LIFE.
>> YEAH.
I AM BEAUTIFUL.
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
>> YEAH.
>> SHE'S BEEN THROUGH A LOT.
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
THESE ARE HAPPY TEARS BUT THEY
>> SHE'S BEEN THROUGH A LOT.
ARE STILL THERE.
THESE ARE HAPPY TEARS BUT THEY
>> TISSUES!
ARE STILL THERE.
WE NEED TISSUES!
>> TISSUES!
WAS!
WE NEED TISSUES!
>> IT'S TOO EARLY FOR ALL THIS.
WAS!
[LAUGHS]
>> IT'S TOO EARLY FOR ALL THIS.
>> IT'S NOT ABOUT SIZE, IT'S
[LAUGHS]
ABOUT SILHOUETTE AND PROPORTION.
>> IT'S NOT ABOUT SIZE, IT'S
WHEN WE WENT SHOPPING, WE DID
ABOUT SILHOUETTE AND PROPORTION.
LOOK AND OF ANY SIZE IS THESE
WHEN WE WENT SHOPPING, WE DID
RACKS.
LOOK AND OF ANY SIZE IS THESE
A PARTIAL SLEEVE DOES THE TRICK
RACKS.
OF GIVING COMFORT BUT IT'S LIGHT
A PARTIAL SLEEVE DOES THE TRICK
AND AIRY, IT'S NOT HEAVY AND
OF GIVING COMFORT BUT IT'S LIGHT
LONG AND YOU ARE SHOWING THE
AND AIRY, IT'S NOT HEAVY AND
MOST BEAUTIFUL PART OF YOUR ARM.
LONG AND YOU ARE SHOWING THE
I CAN'T WAIT TO ASK YOU HOW YOU
MOST BEAUTIFUL PART OF YOUR ARM.
FEEL ABOUT THIS ONE.
I CAN'T WAIT TO ASK YOU HOW YOU
>> Valerie: OH, MY GOODNESS.
FEEL ABOUT THIS ONE.
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
>> Valerie: OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> YOU ARE HERE, YOU ARE LOOKING
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
AT ALL OF THE MOTIF AND YOU
>> YOU ARE HERE, YOU ARE LOOKING
AREN'T EVEN LOOKING TO THIS.
AT ALL OF THE MOTIF AND YOU
WHAT HAPPENS WITH THE SLEEVE, HE
AREN'T EVEN LOOKING TO THIS.
LOOKED BIGGER.
WHAT HAPPENS WITH THE SLEEVE, HE
>> EVEN MORE DEFINED WITH BLING
LOOKED BIGGER.
THIS TIME AROUND.
>> EVEN MORE DEFINED WITH BLING
FITTED BODICE BUT THIS TIME WE
THIS TIME AROUND.
TOOK THE SLEEVE OFF TO ELONGATE,
FITTED BODICE BUT THIS TIME WE
LENGTHEN AND TO GIVE THE
TOOK THE SLEEVE OFF TO ELONGATE,
SLEEVELESS LOOK.
LENGTHEN AND TO GIVE THE
SO, AND A LINE SILHOUETTE IS
SLEEVELESS LOOK.
ACTUALLY UNIVERSAL, BE-ALL
SO, AND A LINE SILHOUETTE IS
CHOICE.
ACTUALLY UNIVERSAL, BE-ALL
THEY ARE SLUMMING TO THE HIPS,
CHOICE.
THEY DEFINE THE WASTE AND
THEY ARE SLUMMING TO THE HIPS,
WHITTLE THE TOP.
THEY DEFINE THE WASTE AND
♪ ♪
WHITTLE THE TOP.
>> Valerie: I NEVER WOULD HAVE
♪ ♪
CHOSEN THIS IS SOMETHING TO TRY
>> Valerie: I NEVER WOULD HAVE
ON.
CHOSEN THIS IS SOMETHING TO TRY
I'M NOT IN GAZILLION YEARS.
ON.
>> HIGH NECK.
I'M NOT IN GAZILLION YEARS.
FIT AND FLARE, TOTALLY DIFFERENT
>> HIGH NECK.
SILHOUETTE, SLIGHT TRAIN.
FIT AND FLARE, TOTALLY DIFFERENT
THIS IS A MAGICAL TRIO FOR YOU.
SILHOUETTE, SLIGHT TRAIN.
>> Valerie: HAVING GRETTA
THIS IS A MAGICAL TRIO FOR YOU.
MONAHAN BY MY SIDE HAS BEEN IN
>> Valerie: HAVING GRETTA
AMERICA AMAZING EXPERIENCE FOR
MONAHAN BY MY SIDE HAS BEEN IN
ME.
AMERICA AMAZING EXPERIENCE FOR
I FEEL LIKE SHE UNDERSTANDS MY
ME.
CONCERNS AND RESPECTS THEM
I FEEL LIKE SHE UNDERSTANDS MY
WHOLEHEARTEDLY.
CONCERNS AND RESPECTS THEM
>> WE HAVE ONE MORE DRESS
WHOLEHEARTEDLY.
BECAUSE WE WANT TO MAKE SURE IS
>> WE HAVE ONE MORE DRESS
SURE.
BECAUSE WE WANT TO MAKE SURE IS
WOW.
SURE.
THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO SAY.
WOW.
>> IF FEEL SOPHISTICATED AND IT
THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO SAY.
FEELS FUN.
>> IF FEEL SOPHISTICATED AND IT
>> Gr>> Valerie: I HAVE MADE A
FEELS FUN.
DECISION BASED ON THE DRESSES I
>> Gr>> Valerie: I HAVE MADE A
TRIED ON.
DECISION BASED ON THE DRESSES I
I AM OVER THE MOON AND I CAN'T
TRIED ON.
WAIT TO SHOW IT TO MY HUSBAND.
I AM OVER THE MOON AND I CAN'T
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
WAIT TO SHOW IT TO MY HUSBAND.
>> Rachael: SO VALERIE AND
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
MICHAEL ARE BOTH RIGHT HERE AND
>> Rachael: SO VALERIE AND
I WAS JUST COMMENDING HER ON HER
MICHAEL ARE BOTH RIGHT HERE AND
FAMILY, BUT TO TRY ON TO THAT
I WAS JUST COMMENDING HER ON HER
MANY DRESSES AND ONE DAY, I SAID
FAMILY, BUT TO TRY ON TO THAT
I NEED A WHOLE BOTTLE OF WINE
MANY DRESSES AND ONE DAY, I SAID
AND SOME DIM LIGHTING.
I NEED A WHOLE BOTTLE OF WINE
THAT'S NERVE-RACKING.
AND SOME DIM LIGHTING.
>> Valerie: IT REALLY WAS.
THAT'S NERVE-RACKING.
MY WHOLE LIFE JUST FLOODED RIGHT
>> Valerie: IT REALLY WAS.
INTO MY FACE LIKE WHERE AM I,
MY WHOLE LIFE JUST FLOODED RIGHT
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
INTO MY FACE LIKE WHERE AM I,
>> Gretta: YOU KNOW FOR
WHAT'S HAPPENING.
VALERIE, WHEN SHE WENT SHOPPING
>> Gretta: YOU KNOW FOR
THE FIRST TIME TO GET MARRIED
VALERIE, WHEN SHE WENT SHOPPING
SHE WAS 350 POUNDS SO THAT'S
THE FIRST TIME TO GET MARRIED
EVEN OVER A PLUS SIZE GOWN.
SHE WAS 350 POUNDS SO THAT'S
SO WHEN YOU GO INTO THE SHOP,
EVEN OVER A PLUS SIZE GOWN.
AND WE SHARED THIS, YOU WILL BE
SO WHEN YOU GO INTO THE SHOP,
GIVEN ONE, SUE, OR THREE
AND WE SHARED THIS, YOU WILL BE
DRESSES.
GIVEN ONE, SUE, OR THREE
INSTEAD IT WAS, IS THE DRESS YOU
DRESSES.
GET TO HAVE.
INSTEAD IT WAS, IS THE DRESS YOU
SHE SAID THAT ROBBED HER OF HER
GET TO HAVE.
MOMENT WHERE SHE'S A BRIDE AND
SHE SAID THAT ROBBED HER OF HER
HAS ALL THESE CHOICES.
MOMENT WHERE SHE'S A BRIDE AND
>> Valerie: FOR ME, THIS
HAS ALL THESE CHOICES.
JOURNEY BEGAN WHEN I WAS ABOUT
>> Valerie: FOR ME, THIS
12 YEARS OLD AND I WAS
JOURNEY BEGAN WHEN I WAS ABOUT
INTRODUCED TO, GETTINGON A
12 YEARS OLD AND I WAS
DIET.
INTRODUCED TO, GETTINGON A
AND IT BECAME THIS CYCLE OF
DIET.
SUCCESS AND FAILURE.
AND IT BECAME THIS CYCLE OF
YOU LOSE 20 POUNDS AND GAINED
SUCCESS AND FAILURE.
30.
YOU LOSE 20 POUNDS AND GAINED
THEN LOSE 40 POUNDS AND GAINED
30.
60.
THEN LOSE 40 POUNDS AND GAINED
IT GOT TO THE POINT WHERE VERY
60.
CLOSE TO BEFORE, I HAD MET
IT GOT TO THE POINT WHERE VERY
MICHAEL AND I SAID TO MYSELF I
CLOSE TO BEFORE, I HAD MET
NEED TO FIGURE THIS OUT.
MICHAEL AND I SAID TO MYSELF I
I WENT TO SEE A DOCTOR AND HE
NEED TO FIGURE THIS OUT.
TOLD ME THAT I WAS MORBIDLY
I WENT TO SEE A DOCTOR AND HE
OBESE AND THAT WAS THE TURNING
TOLD ME THAT I WAS MORBIDLY
POINT FOR ME.
OBESE AND THAT WAS THE TURNING
BECAUSE I HAD NEVER HEARD THAT
POINT FOR ME.
WORD BEFORE.
BECAUSE I HAD NEVER HEARD THAT
AND I THOUGHT OH, MY GOD, IF I
WORD BEFORE.
GET PREGNANT I WILL BE BEDR
AND I THOUGHT OH, MY GOD, IF I
BEDRIDDEN.
GET PREGNANT I WILL BE BEDR
[APPLAUSE]
BEDRIDDEN.
>> Rachael: SO WHAT MADE YOU
[APPLAUSE]
FALL IN LOVE WITH HER AT ANY
>> Rachael: SO WHAT MADE YOU
SIZE?
FALL IN LOVE WITH HER AT ANY
WHAT WAS THAT JOURNEY LIKE FOR
SIZE?
YOU?
WHAT WAS THAT JOURNEY LIKE FOR
>> WE KIND OF GOT PUSHED
YOU?
TOGETHER TO PLAY POOL BY AN
>> WE KIND OF GOT PUSHED
OLDER GENTLEMAN.
TOGETHER TO PLAY POOL BY AN
>> Rachael: WHO WON?
OLDER GENTLEMAN.
>> WE PLAYED TOGETHER.
>> Rachael: WHO WON?
THEN WE STARTED TALKING AND
>> WE PLAYED TOGETHER.
FOUND THE PERSONALITY AND THE
THEN WE STARTED TALKING AND
SIZE DOES MATTER.
FOUND THE PERSONALITY AND THE
>> Rachael: AND HOPEFULLY, A
SIZE DOES MATTER.
GOOD POOL PLAYER?
>> Rachael: AND HOPEFULLY, A
>> Valerie: WELL, [LAUGHTER]
GOOD POOL PLAYER?
>> Rachael: LETS STOP THERE.
>> Valerie: WELL, [LAUGHTER]
[LAUGHS]
>> Rachael: LETS STOP THERE.
SO YOU SAID YOU HAD THIS UPENDED
[LAUGHS]
DOWN, IT WAS LIKE A
SO YOU SAID YOU HAD THIS UPENDED
ROLLER COASTER AND YOU ENDED ON
DOWN, IT WAS LIKE A
A HIGH NOTE?
ROLLER COASTER AND YOU ENDED ON
>> Gretta: SO EXCITED.
A HIGH NOTE?
AND I WANT TO TELL YOU THIS,
>> Gretta: SO EXCITED.
RACHAEL.
AND I WANT TO TELL YOU THIS,
THE DRESS THAT SHE CHOSE, IT WAS
RACHAEL.
COMPLETELY THE OPPOSITE OF THE
THE DRESS THAT SHE CHOSE, IT WAS
LIST OF THINGS THAT SHE SAID SHE
COMPLETELY THE OPPOSITE OF THE
WOULD NEVER DO.
LIST OF THINGS THAT SHE SAID SHE
SO, KEEP AN OPEN MIND AND WAIT
WOULD NEVER DO.
UNTIL YOU SEE WHAT SHE PICKED.
SO, KEEP AN OPEN MIND AND WAIT
>> Rachael: ALL RIGHT, YOU
UNTIL YOU SEE WHAT SHE PICKED.
HAVE FUN GETTING READY.
>> Rachael: ALL RIGHT, YOU
YOU HAVE TO GET GUSSIED UP, TOO.
HAVE FUN GETTING READY.
YOU CAN'T COME OUT HERE AND A
YOU HAVE TO GET GUSSIED UP, TOO.
HULA SHIRT, COME ON.
YOU CAN'T COME OUT HERE AND A
GO PREP SO YOU CAN SAY "I DO"
HULA SHIRT, COME ON.
AGAIN.
GO PREP SO YOU CAN SAY "I DO"
[APPLAUSE]
AGAIN.
MY NEXT GUEST IS SUPER CUTE,
[APPLAUSE]
TOO.
MY NEXT GUEST IS SUPER CUTE,
SHE'S A LAUGH RIOT.
TOO.
SHE EXPLAINS HOW SHE KEEPS HER
SHE'S A LAUGH RIOT.
KIDS HEALTHYISH AND WHAT SHE
SHE EXPLAINS HOW SHE KEEPS HER
CALLS HER "DICTATOR LUNCHES."
KIDS HEALTHYISH AND WHAT SHE
THEY ARE ALL OVER INSTAGRAM.
CALLS HER "DICTATOR LUNCHES."
>> I'M GOING TO MAKE THOSE GREEN
THEY ARE ALL OVER INSTAGRAM.
SMOOTHIE MUFFINS.
>> I'M GOING TO MAKE THOSE GREEN
I NEED BANANAS.
SMOOTHIE MUFFINS.
BAKING SODA OR BAKING POWDER, I
I NEED BANANAS.
FORGET THE DIFFERENCE.
BAKING SODA OR BAKING POWDER, I
BUT LET'S JUST THROW THEM BOTH
FORGET THE DIFFERENCE.
IN.
BUT LET'S JUST THROW THEM BOTH
TWO HANDFULS OF SPINACH.
IN.
I OFTENTIMES GET CARRIED AWAY
TWO HANDFULS OF SPINACH.
AND I LIKE TO ADD MORE THAN TWO
I OFTENTIMES GET CARRIED AWAY
HANDFULS.
AND I LIKE TO ADD MORE THAN TWO
BUT IF YOU PUT TOO MUCH SPINACH
HANDFULS.
IN IT'S LIKE YOU CAN NEVER GET
BUT IF YOU PUT TOO MUCH SPINACH
THEM OFF INTO DRIVE.
IN IT'S LIKE YOU CAN NEVER GET
[BLENDER SOUND]
THEM OFF INTO DRIVE.
>> NOT THERE YET.
[BLENDER SOUND]
I HAVE THESE LITTLE DELLA COTTO
>> NOT THERE YET.
SQUASHES WITH SUNFLOWER OIL.
I HAVE THESE LITTLE DELLA COTTO
>> THE OTHER THING ABOUT HEARING
SQUASHES WITH SUNFLOWER OIL.
REAL PEOPLE COOK, YOU ARE
>> THE OTHER THING ABOUT HEARING
SUPPOSED TO CLEAN UP AS YOU GO.
REAL PEOPLE COOK, YOU ARE
HERE IS YOUR QUEUE, GREEN STUFF.
SUPPOSED TO CLEAN UP AS YOU GO.
OH WAIT, WHAT'S GOING ON?
HERE IS YOUR QUEUE, GREEN STUFF.
>> THEY ARE DONE.
OH WAIT, WHAT'S GOING ON?
THEY ARE ON A LITTLE HIGH
>> THEY ARE DONE.
BECAUSE I WAS ROASTING THE
THEY ARE ON A LITTLE HIGH
SQUASH AT 400.
BECAUSE I WAS ROASTING THE
THIS IS COMING TOGETHER NICELY.
SQUASH AT 400.
♪ ♪
THIS IS COMING TOGETHER NICELY.
>> Rachael: RIGHT, THAT'S THE
♪ ♪
BETTER HALF OF JASON BIGS,
>> Rachael: RIGHT, THAT'S THE
"NEW YORK TIMES" BEST-SELLING
BETTER HALF OF JASON BIGS,
AUTHOR AND CONTRIBUTOR TO
"NEW YORK TIMES" BEST-SELLING
"PARENTS MAGAZINE."
AUTHOR AND CONTRIBUTOR TO
PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO OUR SHOW,
"PARENTS MAGAZINE."
ONE HOT MAMA, JENNY MOLLEN.
PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO OUR SHOW,
♪ ♪
ONE HOT MAMA, JENNY MOLLEN.
[LAUGHTER]
♪ ♪
YOUI AM DYING.
[LAUGHTER]
IT TOOK YOU ALL DAY LONG TO MAKE
YOUI AM DYING.
THAT ONE LUNCH?
IT TOOK YOU ALL DAY LONG TO MAKE
>> Jenny: IA SLANTED OUT
THAT ONE LUNCH?
BEFORE HAND AND I SAID, WHERE AM
>> Jenny: IA SLANTED OUT
I GOING WITH THIS?
BEFORE HAND AND I SAID, WHERE AM
[LAUGHS]
I GOING WITH THIS?
>> Rachael: SO TELL ME ABOUT
[LAUGHS]
THIS.
>> Rachael: SO TELL ME ABOUT
>> Jenny: WELL I HAVE A
THIS.
5-YEAR-OLD WHO CONTROLS ME AND
>> Jenny: WELL I HAVE A
MY HOUSE.
5-YEAR-OLD WHO CONTROLS ME AND
SO I LIKE TO PERVADE THESE
MY HOUSE.
LUNCHES, THESE MOVABLE FEASTS
SO I LIKE TO PERVADE THESE
FOR HIM.
LUNCHES, THESE MOVABLE FEASTS
>> Rachael: THAT'S REALLY WHAT
FOR HIM.
THESE ARE.
>> Rachael: THAT'S REALLY WHAT
>> Jenny: LET I'M NO COOK,
THESE ARE.
LET'S BE CLEAR.
>> Jenny: LET I'M NO COOK,
IF YOU ARE AT MY HOUSE HE WOULD
LET'S BE CLEAR.
BE SO HUMILIATED.
IF YOU ARE AT MY HOUSE HE WOULD
THE FIRE ALARM GOES OFF EVERY
BE SO HUMILIATED.
TIME I TRIED THIS.
THE FIRE ALARM GOES OFF EVERY
>> Rachael: DO YOU KNOW HOW
TIME I TRIED THIS.
MANY SETS I HAVE SET ON FIRE?
>> Rachael: DO YOU KNOW HOW
I EVEN SET ADMIRAL'S SET ON
MANY SETS I HAVE SET ON FIRE?
FIRE.
I EVEN SET ADMIRAL'S SET ON
SO HOW DID YOU RAISE THIS CHILD
FIRE.
THAT WANTS A DELLA COTTO SQUASH
SO HOW DID YOU RAISE THIS CHILD
FOR LUNCH?
THAT WANTS A DELLA COTTO SQUASH
>> WELL AS A PARENT IT ALL HAS
FOR LUNCH?
TO DO WITH YOUR OWN CHILDHOOD
>> WELL AS A PARENT IT ALL HAS
DEFICIT.
TO DO WITH YOUR OWN CHILDHOOD
IF YOU WANT TO MAKE UP FOR WHAT
DEFICIT.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE.
IF YOU WANT TO MAKE UP FOR WHAT
I NEVER HAD LUNCHES PREPARED FOR
YOU DIDN'T HAVE.
ME AS A KID.
I NEVER HAD LUNCHES PREPARED FOR
I HAD TWO WORKING PARENTS AND
ME AS A KID.
WHEN IT CAME TIME FOR HIM TO GO
I HAD TWO WORKING PARENTS AND
TO SCHOOL I WAS LIKE, YOU KNOW
WHEN IT CAME TIME FOR HIM TO GO
WHAT?
TO SCHOOL I WAS LIKE, YOU KNOW
I DON'T TAKE THERE SHOULD BE A
WHAT?
CHILDREN'S MENU.
I DON'T TAKE THERE SHOULD BE A
I THINK IF WE ARE DUMBING DOWN
CHILDREN'S MENU.
FOOD FOR KIDS, WE WILL KEEP DUMB
I THINK IF WE ARE DUMBING DOWN
FOOD.
FOOD FOR KIDS, WE WILL KEEP DUMB
SO I SHOWED HIM EVERYTHING.
FOOD.
I'M NOT INVESTED IN HOW MUCH HE
SO I SHOWED HIM EVERYTHING.
IT'S BECAUSE I WANT TO EXPOSE
I'M NOT INVESTED IN HOW MUCH HE
HIM.
IT'S BECAUSE I WANT TO EXPOSE
AND, I'D THINK THEY CAN BECOME
HIM.
PICKY EATERS.
AND, I'D THINK THEY CAN BECOME
SO HOW COMPLICATED IS IT TO
PICKY EATERS.
SERVE THE LUNCH.
SO HOW COMPLICATED IS IT TO
YOU HAVE TO HAVE ASSISTANT FROM
SERVE THE LUNCH.
THE TEACHING ASSISTANT FOR THE
YOU HAVE TO HAVE ASSISTANT FROM
TEACHER?
THE TEACHING ASSISTANT FOR THE
>> PRESCHOOL WAS AWESOME AND
TEACHER?
WOULD REHEAT FOR ME BUT MY
>> PRESCHOOL WAS AWESOME AND
HUSBAND SCREAMED AT ME ONE DAY
WOULD REHEAT FOR ME BUT MY
BECAUSE HE SAID, JENNY, HE SENT
HUSBAND SCREAMED AT ME ONE DAY
AN AVOCADO WITH A GIANT PIT IN
BECAUSE HE SAID, JENNY, HE SENT
IT AND YOU EXPECTED HIM TO DO
AN AVOCADO WITH A GIANT PIT IN
WHAT WITH THAT?
IT AND YOU EXPECTED HIM TO DO
>> I SAID, I THOUGHT THEY WOULD
WHAT WITH THAT?
TAKE THE PIT OUT.
>> I SAID, I THOUGHT THEY WOULD
AND HE SAID, YOU ARE OVERCOME
TAKE THE PIT OUT.
BULLET HATING THINGS.
AND HE SAID, YOU ARE OVERCOME
>>> Rachael: WE HAVE SOME WARM
BULLET HATING THINGS.
AND FUZZY TIPS FROM OUR CRAZY
>>> Rachael: WE HAVE SOME WARM
FRIEND.
AND FUZZY TIPS FROM OUR CRAZY
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK, RIGHT
FRIEND.
AFTER THIS.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK, RIGHT
>> Announcer: NEXT RACHAEL.
AFTER THIS.
>> Rachael: IT YOU ARE FIRE
>> Announcer: NEXT RACHAEL.
TODAY.
>> Rachael: IT YOU ARE FIRE
>> Announcer: YOU CAN HANDLE
TODAY.
THE TRUTH.
>> Announcer: YOU CAN HANDLE
>> IT'S HARD TO WALK AROUND AND
THE TRUTH.
FIND SOMETHING WE NEED TO FIND
>> IT'S HARD TO WALK AROUND AND
SOMETHING.
FIND SOMETHING WE NEED TO FIND
>> THE SINGLE TIP WILL MAKE A
SOMETHING.
DIFFERENCE TO CLUTTER.
>> THE SINGLE TIP WILL MAKE A
DON'T PUT IT DOWN, PUT IT AWAY.
DIFFERENCE TO CLUTTER.
THEN, SUNNY HOSTIN DISSECTS HER
DON'T PUT IT DOWN, PUT IT AWAY.
NEW SHOW.
THEN, SUNNY HOSTIN DISSECTS HER
"TRUT"TRUTH AND MURDER."
NEW SHOW.
>> I WILL TRY ANYTHING NEW BUT
"TRUT"TRUTH AND MURDER."
I'M ALWAYS PAYING FOR IT.
>> I WILL TRY ANYTHING NEW BUT
>> EMBRACED PEOPLE FOR THEIR
I'M ALWAYS PAYING FOR IT.
DIFFERENCES AND THEN DON'T GO
>> EMBRACED PEOPLE FOR THEIR
OUT TO EAT WITH THEM ANYMORE.
DIFFERENCES AND THEN DON'T GO
>> AND TRUTHFULLY
If your dishwasher doesn't get
dishes completely dry...
try Finish Jet-Dry's NEW
stronger formula.
It dries 100% better than
detergent alone - even plastics.
Get dishes drier than you ever
thought possible.
Try Finish Jet-Dry.
♪ ♪
>> Rachael: OKAY.
WE ARE BACK WITH
"THE NEW YORK TIMES"
BEST-SELLING AUTHOR.
THIS IS AN ASSIGNMENT.
THIS IS JENNY MOLLEN AND I AM
EATING, I DON'T KNOW WHAT I -- A
SKINLESS FRUIT?
>> Jenny: PERSIMMON.
>> Rachael: IT'S A DRIED FRUIT
WITH ALL THE SKIN ON, IT'S A
COMPANY CALLED "RIND?"
>> Jenny: I'M OBSESSED WITH
THIS.
I AM OBSESSED WITH PERSIMMON.
AND WHO KNEW?
I'M ACTUALLY GETTING ALL THE
VITAMINS I'M SUPPOSED TO GET
FROM THIS FRUIT.
KIWI SKIN ISN'T THAT BAD.
I'VE NEVER BEEN INTO KIWI
BECAUSE IT'S SO MUCH EFFORT TO
GET TO THE FRUIT.
BUT NOW -- YOU EAT IT LIKE AN
APPLE.
IT'S AMAZING.
>> Rachael: I ONLY LIKE UNDER
RIPE FRUIT SO I CAN PROBABLY
ROLE TO THIS.
>> Jenny: YOU WILL BE INTO
THIS.
>> Rachael: IT'S FUN.
>> Jenny: AND IT MAKES YOU
VERY REGULAR I WILL ADD TO.
>> Rachael: IT DOES, IT DOES.
[LAUGHS]
BUT YOU KNOW, IT'S ALL GOOD DOWN
THERE.
>> AND THESE YOU DON'T LIKE.
>> THESE I TRIED OVER THE BREAK
AND I LIKE ANYTHING DARK GREEN.
I LOVE LEAFY GREENS AND I LIKED
KALE BEFORE KALE WAS COOL.
SHE SAID THESE ARE VITAMIN
BITES.
AND I'M LIKE, I TOOK MY VITAMINS
BUT WHY NOT HAVE MORE?
POPPED ONE IN MY MOUTH.
UNLIKE DELICIOUS, DELICIOUS,
DELICIOUS.
HALFWAY THROUGH I'M LIKE, SOAP,
SOAP, SOAP.
I DID THAT THING HALFWAY THR
THROUGH.
SO WHAT ARE THE BENEFITS OF THIS
VERSE IS THAT?
IS THIS WAS IN A BOTTLE AND IT
WAS A BOTTLE OF VITAMINS, WHAT
WITH THE PROMISE ON THE BOTTLE
BE?
>> Jenny: THIS IS HEALTHY SKIN
AND NAILS, THIS HAS THE
SPIRALING ALL OF THE NEW AGE
TYPE THINGS.
>> Rachael: AND TO KEEP YOUR
DIGESTIVE TRACT BALANCE?
>> Jenny: AND ALSO TO KEEP US
AS YOUNG AS POSSIBLE.
>> WELL I MAY RETHINK THESE.
[LAUGHS]
LET'S JUST HAVE THE BOTTLE.
NOW SOMETIMES, TODAY IS A GOOD
DAY.
WE GET A SMATTERING OF MEN IN
HERE, LIKE A HALF A DOZEN OR SO.
BUT THERE IS A VERY GOOD LOOKING
MAN THE MIDDLE OF OUR STAGE.
HIS NAME IS HUNTER.
>> Jenny: YES, THAT HUNTER
CRINE.
>> Rachael: ACTUALLY GO OVER
AND SAY HELLO?
>> Hunter: SO NICE TO MEET
YOU.
>> Rachael: SO WHAT IS
PERFORMANCE HOUSE?
>> Hunter: I'M A TEAM OF THREE
PHYSICAL THERAPISTS WITHIN
PERFORMANCE HOUSE AND I TRAIN
THE PEOPLE WE TAKE IN.
SO IF JENNY WANTS TO PLAY WITH
HER KIDS AND BE ABLE TO RUN AND
WE WERE ABLE TO COME UP WITH A
PROGRAM TO STRENGTHEN HER FOR
THE LONG TERM.
>> Rachael: SO WHAT ARE YOU
GUYS DOING HERE?
>> Hunter: CORE FUNCTION IS
ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT
THINGS.
BUILDING YOUR CORE AND HOW THE
REST OF THE BODY IS GOING TO
WORK.
IT >> Jenny: ESPECIALLY AFTER
KIDS.
THE ONE I DON'T HAVE KIDS BUT I
HAVE A PITBULL SO I'M GOOD
THERE.
>> Hunter: SO TOSS THIS.
>> SO THIS IS BUILDING YOUR CORE
STRENGTH?
HOW HEAVY ARE YOUR MEDICINE
BALLS?
>> Hunter: I BROUGHT A LIGHT
ONE BECAUSE WE LIKE TO TAKE
AND BUILD FROM THERE.
>> Rachael: HOW MANY TIMES A
WEEK DO YOU TRAIN?
>> Hunter: 2-3.
>> Jenny: I WAS GOING TO LIE
TO YOU GUYS BUT -- [LAUGHS]
>> Rachael: I FEEL LIKE IF YOU
SAY FIVE OR SIX IT'S NOT AN
ACHIEVABLE GOAL FOR MOST PEOPLE.
>> Hunter: EVERYONE NEEDS TO
START WITH WHAT THEY HAVE.
YOU SET GOALS AND WORK UP TO
WHAT YOU CAN HANDLE.
>> Rachael: ACTUALLY THIS WAS
FUN EXCEPT FOR THAT GREEN THING,
JENNY.
BUT OF COURSE, CHECK OUT
"PARENTS MAGAZINE."
AND THANK YOU, HUNTER.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: UP NEXT, WHAT'S
REALLY COOL IS NOT ONLY ARE WE
TALKING ABOUT HUMANS GETTING
HEALTHIER AND A WOMAN
CELEBRATING HER 187-POUND WEIGHT
LOSS, UP NEXT YOU WILL MEET A
DOG THAT LOST 100 POUNDS.
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Rachael: OKAY.
AS I SAID OVER THE BREAK WE ARE
CELEBRATING HEALTH AND WELLNESS
AND TRANSFORMATIONS TODAY.
WE STARTED WITH A 187-POUND
HUMAN WEIGHT LOSS AND NOW WE ARE
GOING TO MEET I AND INSPIRING
DOG BECAUSE THIS DOG LOST
100 POUNDS.
LET'S HEAR THE STORY.
>> I AM PAM AND I AM THE MOM OF
A GOLDEN RETRIEVER SIBERIAN
HUSKY CROSS NAMED XP 43 WOW KAI.
WHEN I MET HIM HE WEIGHED
142 POUNDS.
DESPITE THE PHYSICAL PROBLEMS IT
WAS CAUSING HIM, HE WAS STILL
THE HAPPIEST HE HAD EVER BEEN.
I NEEDED TO HELP HIM REGAIN HIS
HEALTH.
AT FIRST HE HAD TO WALK ONLY
SHORT DISTANCES TO STOP AND
REST.
MORE OFTEN THAN NOT, OUR
JOURNEYS OUTSIDE ENDED UP WITH
KAI NEEDING TO BE CARRIED BACK
INTO THE HOUSE.
WE STARTED HIM ON THE WATER
TREADMILL IN ADDITION TO OUR
DAILY WALKS.
THE WATER TREADMILL HELPED WITH
HIS STAMINA AND WAS A WAY FOR
HIM TO BE ABLE TO EXERCISE
WITHOUT PUTTING A LOT OF STRESS
ON HIS JOINTS.
IN JUST UNDER ONE YEAR, KAI WAS
ABLE TO LOSE 100 POUNDS.
NOW HE HAS REGAINED ALL THE
THINGS THAT A REGULAR DOG CAN
DO.
I COULDN'T BE MORE PROUD OF HIM
AND HIS DEDICATION AND HIS
DETERMINATION TO LOSE WEIGHT WAS
OVERWHELMING.
HE IS TRULY AN AMAZING DOG.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: PLEASE WELCOME KAI
AND PAM.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: HI, KAI.
HI, PAM.
IT'S ALL SO NICE TO MEET YOU.
AND HE WAS LITERALLY SAVED FROM
BEING PUT DOWN?
>> Pam: I DID IT.
I FOSTERED HIM AND WHEN I GOT
HIM HE WAS 173.
TODAY AND FOR THE PAST THREE
MONTHS HE HAS A WAY TO POUNDS.
THOUGH HE IS ACTUALLY LOST
105 POUNDS.
>> Rachael: YOU KNOW MY DOG IS
A 14-YEAR-OLD RED NOSE PIT BULL
AND SHE DOES NOT WATER THERAPY
TO KEEP HER HEALTH.
SHE DOESN'T FIGHT WEIGHT BUT SHE
FIGHTS A LOT OF OTHER THINGS.
ARTHRITIS AND A SPINAL AND
INJURY.
>> Pam: HE IS SUPPOSED TO BE
11, AND WE DID SCREENING FOR
HEALTH ISSUES BECAUSE HE COULD
LITERALLY WALK FIVE OR TEN
STEPS.
>> Rachael: IT'S JUST LIKE
WITH HUMANS, IT'S EXTRA STRESS
ON AVERAGE ORGAN IN THE BODY AND
IT'S HORRIBLE FOR YOUR JOINTS.
HE'S A MIRACLE.
>> Pam: IT IS.
AND HE DOES HAVE A FEW LONG-TERM
ISSUES FROM HAVING BEEN THAT
WEIGHT.
>> Rachael: BUT TO HAVE A DOG
THAT IS OVER 11 YEARS OLD THAT
WANTS TO PLAY AND GO OUT TO THE
AUDIENCE, HE'S WAGGING HIS TAIL
AND HE'S FULL OF ENERGY.
I HONESTLY THINK THAT ANIMALS
MAKE US BETTER HUMANS.
YOU KNOW?
[APPLAUSE]
>> Pam: THE BEST THING THAT I
LEARNED FROM KAI IN THIS WHOLE
JOURNEY IS, NO MATTER WHAT THE
DAY BEFORE HAD BEEN LIKE, HE
DIDN'T FOCUS ON THAT DAY.
HE GOT UP EVERY DAY AND HE WAS
HAPPY TO WORK REALLY HARD ON THE
SAME GOAL OVER AND OVER.
HE STAYED MOTIVATED AND HE DID
ALL THE HARD WORK.
>> Rachael: AND THAT'S THE
THING.
THEY DO BRING OUT THE BEST IN
US.
>> Pam: I ALWAYS JOKE, IF YOU
WANT A WEIGHT LOSS PROGRAM, GET
AN OVERWEIGHT PET AND AWAY YOU
GO.
AND I THINK THAT'S A REALLY GOOD
IDEA, TOO.
>> Rachael: SO I JUST HAVE TO
SAY, BECAUSE OF NUTRISH AND
EVERYONE THAT HELPS US MAKE OUR
PET FOOD FOR DOGS AND CATS, A
LIKE FOR EVERY AGE AND PHASE OF
THEIR LIVES AND EVERY DIET THEY
MIGHT ENJOY, WE'VE RAISED I
THINK ABOUT $30 MILLION NOW FOR
NONKILL SHELTERS.
[APPLAUSE]
ANYTHING HE WANTS THAT WE MAKE,
WE WILL DELIVER TO YOUR HOME.
YOU PICK AND CHOOSE.
>> Pam: THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> Rachael: I AM SO PROUD OF
YOU!
>> Pam: HE IS AMAZING.
>> Rachael: GO HUG AND ANIMAL!
AND WASH HER HANDS, I WILL MEET
YOU IN THE KITCHEN.
MUSICAL PHYSICAL >> Announcer:
STILL AHEAD, SHE LOST THE WEIGHT
AND NOW WE ARE MAKING HER LOOK
GREAT.
YOU ARE GOING TO SAY "WOW" WHEN
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: THIS IS A FUN AND
HEALTHY -- THAT OUR WORLD FOR
OUR MAGAZINE.
EVERY ISSUE I WRITE 10:30 MINUTE
MEALS AND A BOM, BURGER OF THE
MONTH.
THIS IS A THAI STYLE CORN AND
RED CURRY SOUP.
IT'S GREAT TO MAKE THIS TIME OF
YEAR BEFORE ALL THAT GREAT AND
DELICIOUS SWEET CORN GOES AWAY.
WHEN WE ARE WORKING WITH CORN
AND WANT TO REMOVE IT FROM THE
KAABA, THE BEST METHOD IS TO
INVERT A SMALL BOWL INSIDE A
LARGER GLASS MIXING BOWL AND USE
THAT AS A STAND.
BUT THE EARS ON END AND SCRAPE
DOWN, TRYING TO RETRIEVE ALL OF
THE MILK AND THE KERNELS FROM
THE.
THE LARGER BOWL WILL COLLECT ALL
OF THE KERNELS AND KEEP THE
MAJORITY OF THEM FROM FLYING ALL
OVER THE COUNTER.
SO YOU TAKE SEVERAL YEARS OF
CORN, FIVE OR SIX BIG EARS OF
CORN AND, I SCRAPE THEM ALL DOWN
AND I PUT HALF INTO A
HIGH-POWERED BLENDER OR FOOD
PROCESSOR WITH A LITTLE WATER
AND PUREE THAT.
OR NOT.
IMAGINE IT'S PUREEING.
THERE IS SERIOUSLY NO POWER.
OH, LET'S TURN IT ON.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Rachael: WHATEVER.
IT HAS TWO BUTTONS ON THE FRONT
AND IT'S HIDING ONE UP THE REAR
HERE.
THIS IS A TRICKY LITTLE GUY.
ANYWAY, YOU YOU PUREE HALF OF
THE CORN.
MEANWHILE IN THE BOTTOM OF OUR
SOUP POT, I STARTED OUR SOUP
WITH THESE INGREDIENTS HERE.
SWEET AND HOT PEPPERS.
THIS TIME OF YEAR YOU GET THE IS
THAT BEAUTIFUL FIELD PEPPERS OR
ITALIAN FRYING PEPPERS.
YOU WANT A COMBINATION OF MILD
PEPPERS AND SPICY FRESH RED
CHILIS AND LEAKS.
REALLY AROMATIC AND BEAUTIFUL.
TO THIS SIMPLE COMBINATION THAT
I'M SWEATING OUT IN A LITTLE BIT
OF OIL, ANY HIGH-TEMPERATURE OIL
OR OIL YOU CAN SEE THROUGH, YOU
WANT TO USE A NEUTRAL OIL.
ANY OIL YOU CAN SEE THROUGH WILL
HAVE A VERY MILD FLAVOR.
NOW WE PUT OUR GREATER RIGHT
OVER THE POT AND GREAT IN SOME
FRESH GINGER.
GINGER'S BEST FRIEND IS GARLIC.
I LOVE GARLIC AND I PUT IT IN
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN A TOTAL
JAILBREAK OR TO DATE A MAN WHO
DIDN'T LIKE GARLIC BECAUSE I
ALWAYS SMELLED LIKE SALAMI.
IT'S VERY TRUE.
GARLIC COMES OUT OF YOUR PORES.
IT'S VERY GOOD FOR YOU BUT IT'S
VERY POTENT.
AND I REALLY DO SMELL LIKE
GARLIC.
SO WE ADD OUR GARLIC AND ARE
GINGER.
THEN WE STIR IN OUR RED CURRY
PASTE.
YOU CAN FIND THIS SHELF STABLE
IN GLASS JARS OR EVEN CANS, I'VE
SEEN IT.
OR I BUY THE REFRIGERATED IN THE
TUB IS.
IT'S LIKE RED MISOND WHITE
MISO, AT LAST FOR WEEKS AND
WEEKS.
AND I LIKE THAT IT WAS FRESHLY
MADE.
SO STIR IN A COUPLE OF FAT
SPOONFULS OF YOUR CURRY PASTE.
THIS IS SUCH A FRAGRANT DISH, I
JUST LOVE IT.
FOR YOUR ASSAULT, YOU ADD A
SPLASH OF FISH SAUCE.
LISTEN.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE THAI FOOD OR
YOU RARELY COOK IT AT HOME.
DON'T INVEST IN A GIANT BOTTLE.
YOU COULD THROW IN SOME SOY
SAUCE OR LI LIQUID AMINO, OR SOE
TAMARI.
HERE TODAY, GONE TO MURRAY.
[LAUGHS]
SO WE HAVE OUR NATURAL SALT,
FRAGRANT CURRY, WE HAVE OUR
GARLIC AND OUR GGER.
WE ADD 115-OUNCE CAN OF LIGHT
COCONUT MILK FOR SWEETNESS.
AND, 1 QUART OF CHICKEN,
VEGETABLE OR SEAFOOD STOCK.
YOUR PREFERENCE.
WE ARE GOING TO LEAVE THE REST
OF OUR CORN, THE KERNELS, WHOLE
TO GET THE SOUP TEXTURE.
AND WE ARE GOING TO ADD OUR
PUREE TO GIVE IT SOME VISCOSITY.
WE ARE GOING TO LET ALL OF THIS
COME UP TO A BUBBLE, A LOW,
ROLLING BOIL, AND THEN WE WILL
COOK THE SHRIMP, RIGHT AFTER
THIS.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
Don't eat them for the 100
percent whole grain oats.
THIS.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
Don't eat them because the oats
can help lower cholesterol.
Eat them for her.
♪
What's this?
Cindy, that cold's gonna keep
you up all night.
And tomorrow, you're gonna be a
zombie!
Forget that, I'm taking a new
nighttime cold medicine.
HA! There's nothing new.
'Fraid so.
New Mucinex Nightshift Cold &
Flu fights my worst symptoms
so I can sleep great and wake up
human.
So, you don't want to be zombie.
No, I've gotta work tomorrow. !
New Mucinex Nightshift Cold &
Flu.
Uniquely formulated to fight
your worst symptoms so you can
sleep great and wake up human.
Pets know what they want,
and so do we.
That's why you'll
find real meat,
poultry or fish
and wholesome veggies
in delicious
Rachael Ray Nutrish recipes.
Rachael Ray Nutrish.
Guys! I said I'd be back.
Real Recipes.
Real Ingredients.
Real Good.
You know what?
The way you care
for your baby...
(phone ring-tone plays)
Is absolutely perfect.
And that inspired
our perfect diaper,
our softest yet
with trusted protection.
New Huggies Special Delivery®.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
WE HAVE OUR THAI STYLE CORN
CHCHOWDER HERE, IT'S ACTUALLY LE
A RED CURRY WITH COCONUT MILK,
YOUR CHOICE OF VEGETABLE OR
SEAFOOD STOCK.
THAT'S BUBBLING OVER HERE AND WE
LEFT SOME CORN KERNELS THERE TO
GIVE IT TEXTURE.
NOW WE WILL COOK OUR SHRIMP IN
THE POT OF SIMMERING SOUP.
SO LET'S DROP IN, I WOULD SAY A
FAT HANDFUL PER PERSON PER
PORTION.
WHAT SIZE SHRIMP SHOULD YOU BUY,
IT SHOULD REALLY BE ABOUT WHAT
LOOKS FRESHEST.
I KNOW THIS SOUNDS WEIRD BUT I
ALWAYS ASKED TO SMELL THE SHRIMP
SO I KNOW THAT THE SHRIMP
DOESN'T HAVE A METALLIC AROMA TO
IT.
I DO.
EVERY SINGLE TIME.
THEN WHEN YOU BRING IT HOME OF
COURSE DEEP VEIN IT AND PULLED
THE TAIL OFF.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE EATING
SCALDING HOT SOUP AND TRYING TO
TAKE THE TAIL OFF.
SO WE GET THIS IN THERE AND WE
TAKE A COUPLE OF MINUTES UNTIL
THEY ARE OPAQUE, FIRM AND PINK.
WE LET THAT HANG OUT.
NOW LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
TOPPINGS OR THE ACCOMPANIMENTS.
WE WILL SERVE LIME JUICE OF
COURSE TO SERVE WITH OUR
BEAUTIFUL THAI DISH, VERY
COMMON.
IN ANOTHER VERY COMMON TIE
COMBINATION, MINT AND TYVEK THAI
BASIL.
I LOVE FRESH BASIL.
I TAKE OUT ANY OF THE WOODIER
STEMS.
ANY FINE STEMS ARE JUST FINE BUT
THESE WOODIER PIECES I PULL AWAY
AND MAKE A FAT LITTLE PILE.
WHEN IT COMES TO BASIL OF ANY
TYPE, THAI BASIL OR SWEET BASIL.
WHEN YOU BRING IT HOME FROM THE
STORE, BASIL DOES NOT LIKE
REFRIGERATION.
NEVER PUT IT IN THE
REFRIGERATOR.
KEEP IT ON THE COUNTERTOP JUST
LIKE FRESH-CUT FLOWERS.
CHANGE THE WATER EVERY FEW DAYS.
AND IF YOU KEEP IT IN A LITTLE
PLASTIC STORAGE BAG IT MAKES A
LITTLE GREEN HOUSE FOR THE BASIL
AND IT STAYS NICE AND GREEN
UNTIL YOU ARE USING ALL OF IT.
THAI BASIL IS VERY SIMILAR TO
SWEET BASIL.
SO IF YOU CAN'T FIND IT, OF
COURSE SUBSTITUTE WHAT YOU ARE
HAS.
CILANTRO IS ALSO LOVELY.
FRESH CORIANDER, YOU COULD THROW
INTO THE MIX IF YOU LIKE.
WHEN IT COMES TO CHILIS, I USE
SPICY BIRDSEYE OR LITTLE FINGER
PEPPERS IN THE SOUP ITSELF.
REMEMBER WE PUT IN SWEET PEPPERS
AND HOT PEPPERS.
I LIKE TO FLOAT FOR GARNISH
SLICES OF FRESNO CHILIS.
THEY ARE A FRUITY AND MILD HEAT
AND THEY ARE BEAUTIFUL TO FLOAT
ON T TOP OF SOUPS.
THEY ARE NOT TOO HEAVY TO SINK
AND THEY ARE NOT TOO SPICY, IT'S
MORE OF A FRUITY, ACIDIC MILD
HEAT.
SO WE HAVE SOME FINELY CHOPPED
CHILIS.
MY FRIEND JEANETTE IS OBSESSED,
ESPECIALLY SINCE THIS IS UPTIGHT
CHOWDER, SHE IS OBSESSED WITH
OYSTER CRACKERS.
SO I HAVE A COPIOUS AMOUNT OF
OYSTER CRACKERS TO SERVE.
SO I WILL LET THE FRESH, COULD
SHRIMP FINISH AND WE WILL COME
SHRIMP FI've been saying, COME
BACK A     “I'm fine.”
But, really I'm struggling to
keep up this brave face...
to hide my symptoms
of depression.
I'm taking my antidepressant
like we discussed.
But, I'm still feeling
depressed.
Is it just me?
It's not just you.
2 out of 3 people
on antidepressants
may still experience symptoms.
When added to an
antidepressant,...
REXULTI has been proven to help
reduce symptoms of depression.
So I can stay on my current
antidepressant...
and help build on the
progress I've made.
REXULTI is not for everyone.
Call your doctor about unusual
changes in behavior,
worsening depression,
or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants can increase
these in those 24 and younger.
Elderly dementia patients
taking REXULTI
have an increased risk
of death or stroke.
Call your doctor if you
have high fever,
stiff muscles, and confusion
to address a possible
life-threatening condition...
or if you have uncontrollable
muscle movements,
as these may be permanent.
REXULTI has been shown
to increase blood sugar
in some people.
Other risks are increased
cholesterol; weight gain;
unusual urges or
compulsive behaviors; ...
decreased white blood cells,
which can be serious; ...
dizziness on standing; seizures;
trouble swallowing;
and impaired judgment
or motor skills.
Now, I'm glad I talked with my
doctor about adding REXULTI.
Feel better about
facing the world.
Pay $0 for your first
REXULTI prescription.
Details at REXULTI.com.
Pay $0 for your first
REXULTI prescription.
I was on the fence about
changing
from a manual to an electric
toothbrush.
But my hygienist said going
electric
could lead to way cleaner teeth.
She said, get the one inspired
by dentists,
with a round brush head.
Go Pro with Oral-B. Oral-B's
gentle rounded brush head
removes more plaque along the
gum line.
For cleaner teeth and healthier
gums.
And unlike Sonicare, Oral-B
is the first electric toothbrush
brand
accepted by the ADA
for its effectiveness and
safety.
What an amazing clean!
I'll only use an Oral-B!
Oral-B.
Brush like a pro.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: OKAY.
THIS IS "TIE IT, YOU'LL LIKE IT"
THAI STYLE CORN CHOWDER.
SUPER SIMPLE, COLORFUL AND
FLAVORFUL.
GINGER, GARLIC, COCONUT MILK,
THE LEAKS, YUM YUM.
THEN WE BRING IT ON DOWNTOWN SO
WE CAN GARNISH IT.
LET ME GET A PAPER TOWEL FOR THE
EDGE.
SO, OUR SHRIMP ARE PERFECTLY
COOKED.
THEY ARE JUST PINK AND OPAQUE.
WE ARE GOING TO ADD A LITTLE
LIME JUICE, VERY TRADITIONAL IN
THAI DISHES OF COURSE AND THEN
THAT WONDERFUL COMBINATION OF
FRESH MINT AND TI TIGHT BASIL.
AND OUR THINLY SLICED, NOT TOO
SPICY FRESH FRESNO CHILIS.
AND FOR JEANETTE, A SPRINKLE OF
OYSTER CRACKERS.
NOW LET ME SHOW YOU THE WAY
JEANETTE WOULD EAT THE SOUP.
[LAUGHTER]
>> Rachael: IF YOU THINK I'M
KIDDING, SHE JUST CAME OUT HERE
AND SAID I WOULD JUST EAT THE
ENTIRE BOWL OF OYSTER CRACKERS
AND PUT A LITTLE SHRIMP AND
JUICE ON TOP.
SO THIS ONE IS  FOR MY FRIEND
JEANETTE!
>> THANK YOU!
>> Rachael: WOULD YOU LIKE
SOME OF THIS?
A LITTLE SQUIRT OF LIME?
>> PLEASE.
THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: IT'S HARD TO TOP A
BOWL OF OYSTER CRACKERS BUT, WE
ARE GOING TO SEE OUR WONDERFUL
COUPLE SAY I DO AGAIN, VALERIE
AND MICHAEL, RIGHT AFTER THIS.
>> Announcer: COMING UP, HERE
COMES THE BRIDE AND GROOM.
OUR WONDROUS WEDDING REDO AND
Trick-or-treat.
♪♪
Bye. Thank you.
Happy Halloween.
What have you got?
♪♪
This is all you bring me
on Halloween?
It's 2 candies in 1.
Gum and lollipops.
[Yawning]
Are you serious?
♪♪
Pleasure doing business
with you.
Yeah... woo.
[wolf howling]
♪♪
SC Johnson.
♪ ♪
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: OKAY.
AS YOU CAN SEE WE ARE ALL SET TO
SAY "I DO" AGAIN.
WE WANT TO THINK PASSION ROSES
WERE DOING SUCH A GREAT JOB AND
A QUICK ONE I MIGHT ADD WITH THE
BEAUTIFUL FLORALS THAT HAVE JUST
LITERALLY GROWN IN OUR STUDIO.
WE WANT TO THANK OUR DEAR FRIEND
GRETTA MONAHAN FOR ADDRESSING
EVERYONE, KLEINFELD BRIDAL FOR
VALERIE'S AMAZING DRESS.
I HAVEN'T SEEN IT YET BUT I HEAR
IT'S HOT.
AND MEN'S WAREHOUSE FOR MICHAEL
SUIT.
THANK YOU FOR TAKING OFF THE
HAWAIIAN SHIRT.
>> YOU ARE WELCOME.
>> Rachael: SARAH RITCHIE IS
OUR EFFICIENT AND NICOLE AND
JAMES ARE HOLDING MOM AND DAD'S
RINGS.
THEY SAY IT'S COOL BECAUSE THEY
MISSED IT THE FIRST TIME.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
>> Rachael: NICOLE ALSO GOT A
FABULOUS MERMAID NAIL POLISH
TODAY AND ALSO REPORTED THAT MOM
MISSED HER BEST FRIEND'S WEDDING
BECAUSE SHE WAS BUSY HAVING HER.
[LAUGHS]
THE KICK IS A GIFT FROM OUR DEAR
FRIEND, THE KICK BOSS HIMSELF,
BUDDY VALASTRO WHO BROUGHT THIS
TO THE STUDIO TODAY.
THANK YOU BUDDY.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY IS STUNNING.
AND I THINK THERE WILL BE KICK
FOR ALL.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
THAT INCLUDES YOU, GRETTA.
ARE YOU HAPPY WITH THE DRESS
THAT SHE CHOSE?
>> Gretta: THEY ALL LOOKED
AMAZING.
SHE PICKED THE ONE THAT SHE
FELT -- AND I LOVED THIS, AND
IT'S ALL SHE HAD TO SAY TO ME.
SHE SAID THIS IS THE MOST ME AND
I WOULD NEVER BE ABLE TO WEAR
THIS BEFORE.
SO IT'S PERFECT, 14 YEARS LATER.
>> Rachael: WELL LET'S GET
THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD!
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Valerie: HI.
>> I AM SO HAPPY TO BE HERE WITH
YOU CELEBRATING YOUR
ANNIVERSARY.
VAL RENEWALS ARE SUCH SPECIAL
OCCASIONS, RETROSPECTIVE GIVING
THANKS FOR GOING THROUGH ALL THE
INDIVIDUAL TRANSITIONS YOU'VE
MADE AS A INDIVIDUAL, COUPLE AND
AS A FAMILY.
YOU'VE KNOWN EACH OTHER SINCE
2002 OVER KARAOKE AND A LITTLE
BIT OF POOL IN WOODSIDE, QUEENS.
14 YEARS AGO YOU DECIDED TO
MARRY AND WE STAND HERE TODAY TO
CELEBRATE WITH YOU ALL THAT YOU
HAVE ACHIEVED AND A BEAUTIFUL
LIFE THAT YOU HAVE LOOKING
FORWARD.
I ASK YOU TO REPEAT VOWS SIMILAR
TO WHAT YOU TOOK ON A SPECIAL
DAY.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO FIRST?
>> Valerie: I VALERIE TAKE YOU
MICHAEL AGAIN TO BE MY HUSBAND.
TO HAVE AND TO HOLD FROM THIS
DAY FORWARD, FOR BETTER OR WO
WORSE.
FOR RICHER OR POORER.
IN SICKNESS AND IN HEALTH.
TO LOVE AND TO CHERISH.
UNTIL WE ARE PARTED BY DEATH.
THIS IS MY SOLEMN VOW.
>> I MICHAEL, TAKE YOU VALERIE,
AGAIN TO BE MY WIFE, TO HAVE AND
TO HOLD IT, FROM THIS DAY
FORWARD.
FOR BETTER OR FOR WORSE, FOR
RICHER OR POORER, IN SICKNESS
AND IN HEALTH, TO LOVE AND TO
CHERISH, UNTIL WE ARE PARTED BY
DEATH.
THIS IS MY SOLEMN VOW.
>> SO YOU'VE BEEN WEARING
WEDDING BANDS ARE SYMBOLS OF THE
PROMISES YOU MADE 13 YEARS AGO
AND THE CIRCULAR SHAPE SIGNIFIED
THAT LOVE HAS A NEITHER A
BEGINNING OR THE END.
THESE ARE OBJECTS  THAT SAY TO
THE WORLD, I LOVE AND I AM
LOVED.
YOUR CHILDREN ARE READY HERE
WITH NEW GIFTS OF RINGS THAT YOU
WILL BE SHARING WITH EACH OTHER.
NICOLE, IF YOU'D LIKE TO GIVE
YOUR FATHER'S RING TO YOUR MOM?
AND REPEAT AFTER ME.
SPEAK TO THIS RING IS MY GIFT TO
YOU.
MAY IT ALWAYS REMIND YOU THAT
NOW AND FOREVER WE WILL BE
SURROUNDED BY MY LOVE.
>> I GUESS I'M SUPPOSED TO PUT
MY FINGER OUT.
[LAUGHTER]
>> VALERIE, THIS RING IS MY GIFT
TO YOU.
MAY IT ALWAYS REMIND YOU THAT
NOW AND FOREVER, YOU WILL BE
SURROUNDED BY MY LOVE.
>> WE LIFT OUR HEARTS IN
THANKSGIVING FOR THE LOVE THAT
YOU FOUND AND TENDED ALL THESE
YEARS.
FOR THE WONDERFUL TRANSITION, WE
FEEL BLESSED TO BE PART OF YOUR
DAY.
WE SEND YOU ON YOUR DAY WISHING
YOU THE SUN MAY SHINE UPON YOU.
THAT THE LOVE YOU HAVE FOR ONE
ANOTHER MAY GROW AND HOLD YOU
CLOSE.
MAY YOU BE A TRUE GUIDING LIGHT
FOR ONE ANOTHER.
WHEN YOUR DREAMS COME TRUE AND
WHEN THEY DO NOT, AND BY THE
POWER INVESTED IN ME BY THE CITY
OF NEW YORK, I WISH YOU THE
BEST.
PLEASE KISS YOUR BRIDE.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
MUSICAL PHYSICAL >> Rachael:
THAT WAS AWESOME!
AND I LOVE THAT NICOLE SAID, HOW
COME DADS RING IS FANCIER THAN
MOMS?
[LAUGHTER]
YOU LOOK SO STUNNING.
DON'T CRY.
YOU LOOK GREAT!
AND I HAVE TO TELL YOU, I AM
CRYING BUT IT'S THANKS TO CHILI
PEPPERS UP MY NOSE.
>> Valerie: NO, IT ISN'T.
[LAUGHS]
>> Rachael: ONE MORE THING
BEFORE YOU CUT YOUR KICK AND EAT
WITH 150 STRANGERS.
WE ARE GOING TO SEND YOU ON A
LITTLE SECOND HONEYMOON IN
BARBADOS.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
>> Rachael: YOU ARE GOING TO
THE SEABREEZE AT BEACH HOUSE, A
FIVE NIGHT ALL-INCLUSIVE STAY IN
A LUXURY OCEANFRONT JUNIOR SUITE
WHERE YOU CAN ENJOY SIX UNIQUE
DINING OPTIONS, THREE POOLS,
1,000 FEET OF BEACHFRONT AND
MORE.
AND YOUR ROUND-TRIP AIRFARE WAS
PROVIDED FOR US BY JETBLUE.
HAVE FUN!
IT'S A PARTY!
THANK YOU AGAIN TO ALL OF OUR
GUEST TODAY AND OUR VERY SPECIAL
COUPLE, VALERIE AT MICHAEL.
THANK YOU GUYS FOR COMING, THIS
WAS SO MUCH FUN.
AND THANK YOU GUYS FOR JOINING
US FOR THEIR WEDDING AGAIN.
AND EVERYBODY, LET'S EAT KICK!
[APPLAUSE]
♪ ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]