And then
I was, like, then I couldn't
scare her too bad, because she
would get mad, so I had to just
like, wait till she found me.
Oh, hello.
[laughter]
- Hello?
[pounding]
[screaming]
- Who is she screaming to?
- Look, dog.
Aunt Mary is about to
literally
attempt to commit suicide.
- Where she going?
- Trying to jump off the--where
are you going?
- She wanted him to kill her.
- You almost scared me to
death, Douglas.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna tell your mother on
you.
- It's just, like, his mom's
friend.
There you have it for Masters
of Horror.
[cheers and applause]
A little thing we call Crowd
end of theControl. her■÷
We're gonna pres■■
applause, we'll let you guys
choose what you want to see.
Let's see what we got.
Would you rather see Traveling
Light?
[applause]
- Would you rather
see Dunk Delight?
[cheers and applause]
Man, you
guys, it's almost like--they
■
were just anti-clapping on
Travelling Light.
Dunk Delight,
let it rip.
Coming in for--
let it go...
Boom!
There you have it, a dunk like
you've never seen.
All right, that's it
for our show.
Thank you to 21 Savage,
Steelo Brim, and Chanel
West Coast.
I'm Rob Dyrdek,
we'll see you next time on
"Ridiculousness."
- ♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Yeah yeah
yeah yeah ♪
♪ ♪
- Where's my cereal?
- They got a new thing called
"freesh avoc-kadoo".
[laughter]
- Now, when you see these kids
just sucking face,
and just, probably--
I'm assuming they're...
getting it in, right?
[laughter]
But at the end
of these seasons,
do these couples
end up together?
Do they find "the one"
in the end?
- Rob, Rob, if they go in at
the angle that you just did,
they're going to find love
at that angle.
Rob went in with the--
- Man, we're going to find love
in the form of this
beautiful little baby.
[laughter]
- You know,
when you're shooting,
and you're isolated, and you're
in a place like Hawaii,
and your emotions
are running high,
you know, you're just
going to find it.
You're going to fall
right into place.
- Yeah, just connect,
and get right back
to the real world and
your [bleep]-ass apartment.
- Yep.
- And [bleep] like--
You know what I'm saying?
I believe in love on TV.
I've seen it happen.
I believe it can happen.
But this first category
is dedicated to those
that probably are never
going to find love,
called Definitely Not The One.
Take a look.
■■■
■■
cal I just want to suck it.ne.
I don't even care.
- Oh, man.
- Oh, it's okay.
I can do the--
oh, oh.
- That's how you know
it's good, though.
When it's dripping
down your mouth.
- How you get it
in your nose, though?
- Because he wanted
to smell it.
He's like ooh, vanilla.
- Get him a hot towel.
■■í■■■■■-oh.
[groovy music]
- Miss, will you
please let me
private message you?
Please, ma'am?
- Okay.
- Oh, man, wait, what?
- Private message you?
- I don't--
that's not how DMs work, sir.
You actually just slide on in.
- Are his underwear cuffed?
Like, what is happening
with his underwear?
It's like, is there
a draw string?
[laughter]
Fat Chris Pratt is wilding.
- Man.
[laughter]
- Hey, I just got dumped,
so, uh, I'm single now.
So does anybody
want to date me?
I'm single and awesome.
- He's got the closer.
- Oh, man.
- And awesome!
Just in case
you wanted to know.
[laughter]
Oh, it's just my hand
and my hand
doing some tourism
in New York City.
- What is he doing?
- He's just--
- Oh, my God.
[groans]
- No!
- Oh, man!
- I'm I the only one
getting anxiety
that he has his phone
that close to the edge?
[laughter]
I'm like, forget the picture.
Don't drop your phone, man.
- But also, is it possible
to take a photo
with your lips and mouth?
- Dude, I've tried that
so many times.
It never works.
- Wait, what the [bleep]?
- What were you attempting to--
what could you not
use a hand for?
Nails?
- Yeah, I think that's what--
I was trying to get my nails.
You're so smart.
- Yeah.
- Or it's the obvious
[bleep] answer.
[laughter]
- Uh-oh.
- Oh, she way too close
to the Ring.
- Derrick.
- Derrick!
- I don't know if
you're getting this,
but, Derrick, if you're single,
hit a sister up!
[laughter]
- There you have it for
Definitely Not The One.
[cheers and applause]
- So, another show
that you host on MTV
is "SafeWord," right?
- Yeah.
- So, you recently had Steelo
on the show, right?
- Yeah.
- And here's the thing
about a show
like "SafeWord," right?
So if, ultimately, you're put
in this compromised position
by your best friend,
and--and like,
you got to pull that SafeWord
if it's too much?
This guy does not care
about anything.
- He's the worst, man.
- Man.
- He doesn't give a [bleep].
All-that's why he won, right?
- Yeah, I won.
- Because he was like,
it didn't matter what it was.
Like, putting his
ex-chick on blast.
It doesn't matter what.
"Post it, I don't care!"
[laughter]
Okay, and the safeword
is for when you're in
a big, terrible situation.
You've got to get yourself out.
Everybody in this next category
is using a word,
then they're slamming.
We call it Unsafe Words.
Take a look.
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
- You're good.
- You're doing a good job!
- I'm doing it!
Oh, it's over.
[groaning]
- Celebrated way too early.
- Man.
- I'm doing it!
- And you can see
where her legs
had like, a little seizure.
Like, look.
That's when it all
went downhill from there.
[laughter]
- Uh-oh.
- Hey, Frank.
Are you up there?
- Bring a trash can, quick.
[groaning]
- Oh, my God.
- He thought he needed
a trash can for that?
- He said--he said--
- What kind of rectangular
trash can do you have?
- You need a bathtub.
- Hey, how much you pay
for that taco?
- ♪ Hey, you know this boy's
got his free taco-- ♪
[groaning]
- Oh, man.
- Was he on a skate--
what happened?
How did he fall?
What?
- I mean, look.
- Now he got no free taco.
- As a man that
spent many years
as a professional skateboarder,
■■■lear sound
of the bearings
of a board that just
got stepped on.
- Got it.
- Right?
So he's doing what I would
consider the free taco dance.
Right, and stepped back.
What we call the banana peel.
And lost his taco,
and probably broke his elbow.
- ♪ Hey, you know this boy's
got his free taco-- ♪
- Free taco--oh!
[groans and laughter]
- Ouch.
- ♪ You ain't got no
free taco, free taco ♪
- ♪ Jingle bells,
jingle bells-- ♪
[groaning]
- Oh.
- Oh, yeah.
Working on his balance skills,
headed to the circus.
♪ Jingle bells, jingle bells,
scorpion all the way ♪
- Ooh.
- You think that fire
is the boss of me?
No, I am the boss of fire.
- No fire's ever going to be
the boss of you.
[groans and laughter]
- Oh, wait, oh.
- Kick it, kick it!
[groans and laughter]
No, I'm sorry,
but fire is the boss of you.
We'll be right back
with more "Ridiculousness."
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ ♪
(Atlas)
Do humans like overpaying
with Verizon?
Don't they know they can get the
3rd, 4th and 5th lines
FREE with Sprint?
(Paul)
Yeah that means Sprint's
Unlimited Plan
gives you 5 lines for just
$20 per month, per line.
(Mom)
Really?
(Atlas)
Yes and you can save
more than $1,000
over Verizon and AT&T
with Sprint.
(Mom)
No way!
(Dad)
Robots don't lie.
(Atlas)
The man in the mom
jeans is correct.
(AVO)
Switch today and get 5 lines
for just $20 per
month per line.
See how you can save more than
For people with hearing loss,
$1,000 in the first year
with Sprint.
visit Sprintrelay.com■■■■Rs
When Taco Bell's
Nacho Fries disappear...
Where did you go?
...one man must bring them back.
♪
♪Daddy's gonna bring
you Nacho Fries... ♪
Now Serving.
[BONG]
Uh-oh!
Guess what day it is?
Guess what day it is!
Huh...anybody?
Julie!
Ah come on, I know
you can hear me.
Mike Mike Mike
Mike Mike...
what day is it Mike?
Ha ha ha ha!
Leslie, guess
what today is?
It's Hump Day.
Whoot Whoot!
Ronny, how happy are folks
who save hundred of dollars
switching to GEICO?
I'd say happier than
a camel on Wednesday.
HUMP DAY!!!
Get happy. Get GEICO.
Fifteen minutes could save
you fifteen percent or more.
You can't put a price on love.
Get happy. Get GEICO.
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
[ gasp ]
No way.
It's Monday the 18th again.
Ah!
I was stuck reliving
the same day.ó■ó■ó■
I thought I ended the loop,
but he's back.
This time the killer is
coming after all of us.
[ gasp ]
[ scream ]
If I die again...
I could stay dead.
Who are you?
[Devo's "Uncontrollable Urge"]
[cheers and applause]
- Welcome back
to "Ridiculousness."
Give it up for our guest,
Terrence J.
- Yeah, yeah.
[cheers and applause]
- Okay, when you auditioned
for "106 & Park,"
did you have to
go multiple places
to actually win the job?
- Absolutely.
- What happened?
- You know, I, um--
I was living in Florida.
I took all my life savings
at the time--
I was just out of college,
flew to New York.
There was a line
of 1,000 people.
I was like, number 700.
I was nervous, I was tired.
They gave you this paper,
and you had to read off of it.
And I was just really bad.
I was inexperienced.
So my boy, he hyped me up.
For real, he was like, yo,
let's just go
to the next audition.
So when we drove
from New York to Atlanta,
I knew what to expect.
So I always tell people,
you know,
you keep hanging around
the barbershop long enough,
you bound to get a cut.
- Yeah, solid.
- Yeah, yeah.
- That was real.
- Okay, look.
You chased your dreams.
You didn't give up.
Just like everybody
in this next category,
because they slam, but they
get up and keep going.
We call ng.
ke a l
.
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
- I want to be a male
cheerleader, and this is my--
[groaning]
No, I'm still here!
- Let's go, let's go!
- I'm still here!
We're talking flawless.
I almost feel like it was
part of the act.
- I mean, that was
a great recovery.
- I mean, really,
does it get any better?
- That was
a Beyoncé recovery, bruh.
[laughter]
[heavy rock music]
- Uh, I'm dead, I'm dead.
No, I'm good.
- Yeah!
- Rob, Rob,
how painful is that?
If you do that?ke, how?
Look, to be honest,
look at his gut.
You know what I mean?
If I land on it,
I'm breaking ribs.
He lands on that
soft little belly,
■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■z
- Yeah!
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
- Coming in hot,
looking for some air.
Got 'em!
[groaning]
Just keep goin■■ñ= eve■
Yo Just keep going.ng.■■a
- EMT, like,
you can't save my life
■ñ■
if you're running like this.
You can't save my life.
- No, no, no.
[laughter]
[groovy music]
- Yeah, hell yeah,
I can breakdance.
[groaning]
I'ma tell you what,
I told y'all.
I've been breaking since '84.
All right, Debbie, watch.
Debbie, this one's
for you, Debbie.
[laughter]
- No--nobody--
- Yeah.
- Nobody wanted to see it!
- Wasn't even looking.
Man, when you want to show
you've got the worm
to the office--
[laughter]
- Bro, bro.
- You never stop worming
until they respect you■■■■■
[laughter]
- Coming right at you.
[cheering]
- Uh-oh, look.
- Oh, no, no.
- It ain't ever over!
It ain't ever over!
[laughter]
- Pushing it over, boy.
- It ain't ever over.
[laughter]
It ain't ever over.
There you have it
for Keep Hustling.
[cheerplause]
- Oh, you missed every--uh!
- All right, Terrence.
You got, uh--two dogs
that have their own Instagram.
Tell us about those guys.
- Yeah, Rocky and Bam Bam.
Funny story, so we were out
drinking one night.
Uh, very responsible drinking.
And I decided
it would be a good idea
for Steelo's dog to come over
and meet my dogs.
So we come--and Steelo's like
"don't bring your dogs over.
It's not going to be good.
You got to introduce dogs
in the right way."
They have to be--
- Steelo getting all technical.
- I'm like,
it's going to be okay,
it's going to be okay.
We walk away from the dogs.
My dog literally has Wrigley's
whole entire head in her mouth.
- Head in her mouth.
- He got one--
I hate to call your--
he got one stupid dog, though.
He was looking at the wall.
[laughter]
- Man, "I don't want
to be disrespectful,
but he's got a dumbass dog."
You know what I'm saying?
But look, in the form
of Steelo's dog
the category Broken Dogs.
that mTake a look.
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
- Oh, look, look, look!
Look at her!
■■■roug
I can get through, I swear!
Ah, ah!
What are y'all doing?
What are you guys doing?
n I sit up here?
- Oh, back up!
- Marissa, back seat.
- No, I'm good.
■■    - He's l■■■■■■■■■■
■■
- Marissa, back seat.
[uegeg'm good.
[groaning]
- How would you
take off that early?
Is he trying to
jump over the shadow?
- I mean, he just--he is.
He legitimate--
I got to get over this.
■And good--oh.
[laughter]
Uh-oh, you don't--
don't you bring
no Swiffer at me.
[laughter]
Oh, not that skateboard now.
- That's Wrigley,
that's Wrigley.
- It don't matter what it is.
If it's pointed at me,
it's dangerous.
- Yep.
- Got it.
- Aw.
- He's going to break a tooth.
- Poor buddy.
- Wait, I'm so confused.
If he can't get it,
who bit the bone first?
[laughter]
- Aw.
- Everybody gets all sad.
Like, aw.
Feed the dumb little guy.
- [warbling human-like barking]
♪ ♪
- I'm having a conversation.
- [barking resumes]
[laughter]
- I mean--
- Walter, I'm right here, baby.
- That's the
actual dog's noise?
- Yeah.
- That's kind of dope, though.
I think, like--
- That--you would not want to
hear that [bleep]
in the middle of the night.
[laughter]
You'd be like
"shut the [bleep] up!"
[laughter]
- I'm having a conversation.
- [barking resumes]
- Walter's got a voice on him.
[groaning]
Go back, go back, go back.
What's he saying?
Who are you?
- Who are you?
- How'd you get--boom!
Okay, that there
is a Broken Dog.
We'll be right back
with more "Ridiculousness."
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ ♪
You can't put a price on love.
But if you did,
it'd cost the exact same
as a Reese's.
Turns out love's kinda
inexpensive.
Not Sorry. Reese's.
■8
■vzO
Go! Enjoy yourselves! I'm pretty
OK with children.
Just OK?
Relax, I'm not gonna forget
anything bedtime's at eleven.
Eight.
Yikes, you're strict...
allergy to shellfish.
Peanuts.
Oh I should write this down.
Hey, what's your wifi password?
It's the names of our kids.
Well that's not helpful.
JUST OK IS NOT OK.
Especially when it comes to your
network.
AT&T is America's best wireless
network,
according to America's biggest
test.
Now with 5
MORE FOR YOU THAT'S OUR
THING.
■7
♪ Always take the risk. ♪
Don't just watch it...
Put your phone down and do it.
♪ Drip splash like the ice
on the wrist. ♪
♪ Brrt brrt brrt brrt ♪
♪ that's a call I can't miss. ♪
Free free, free.
Let's do.
Free. Uh...
Free.
Free...uh. Freefreefree!
Free!
Free. Free! Freefree!
Freefreefreefree!
Free. Free!
Free free. Free! Free!
Fr-free!
Free!!!
Free!
Freefreefree.
FREE...freefree. FREE!
FREE!!!
That's right, TurboTax Free
is free.
Free, free free free.
That's right, TurboTax Free
is free.
[Devo's "Uncontrollable Urge"]
- Welcome back
to "Ridiculousness."
Give it up for our guest,
Terrence J.
- Thanks, dude.
[cheers and applause]
- All right, Terrence,
in your time on "106 and Park,"
is there any videos
that were memorable
that stayed on the countdown
the longest?
- Ja Rule.
Like, "Put It On Me"
was one of my favorite ones.
That was on for a long time.
- Yeah?
- Ja Rule was on there for--
- Yeah.
- Yeah, we had some ones
that were on there
for a really long time.
- Okay, look, we've got this
category of music videos.
Um, but they're [bleep].
[laughter]
And all of them,
no matter when.
Not one moment in time,
not early on, not even today,
would ever make
it to the Countdown.
Take a look
at Not In The Countdown.
[cheers and applause]
[dramatic music]
- Ready?
- Man.
- Let's go!
[groovy music]
♪ Do the beach boogie ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Got to keep grooving ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
- Bruh, how did he
get the volunteers, man?
- Well, we know
this guy's his kid.
- Yeah.
- Turn it up.
- ♪ Do the beach boogie ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Got to keep grooving ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
- That's a hit.
[cheer- It is.
Like, accidentally
got 300 million views--
[groaning]
Yo, hey, hey.
- Can't even--
I'm sorry.
- Look.
You know a guy
can't get a word out
when you see
a giant old woman like this.
[laughter]
Hit it, girls!
- ♪ Big butts, big butts ♪
- ♪ See how we do ♪
- ♪ See how you do ♪
both: ♪ We got something ♪
♪ That it makes you cry ♪
■  ♪ Just blow a kiss ♪
♪ And wave bye-bye ♪
♪ Because big butts rule ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Go back to the drool, because
we have to analyze this drool.
- Yeah, just--
- Is that natural drool?
[groaning]
- She had to put water
in her mouth there.
- Yeah, mouth water.
- I got the
perfect shot, ■■■>■>■■■■■■]
- ♪ Something's holding on ♪
- Oh, my God!
[laughter]
- Man.
- He came in hard.
- He did.
- ♪ Something's holding on ♪
- Ooh, okay.
Everlast.
- ♪ But I know ♪
♪ She wants me back ♪
♪ Because every♪
♪ She tries to wa♪
♪ Something's holding on ♪
♪■ñ♪ What it is right no♪
♪ But I know ♪
♪ She wants me back ♪
- This is my new
favorite video.
- ♪ I know she wants me back ♪
- That's actually hard, yo.
- This is incredible,
.
- I respect commitment.
- He is committed.
- You know what I mean?
Like, it don't matter
if you can't--
you can't find the beat,
the beat's [bleep].
d made
pretty cool cuts
- This--this one might
have made the Countdown.
■
in the top ten.
[tense rock music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Here, I stand-- ♪
- Oh, man.
- ♪ All alone ♪
- Come on, Darryl.
Let it rip!
- ♪ All by myself ♪
- Aurora borealis, Darryl.
- Was she on Facetime
at the end?
[laughter]
- I loved her, I loved her.
- She's on Facetime!
- They were Facetiming.
- Hey, Cindy, good to see you.
Yeah, when's
the homeowner's meeting?
- What was this about?
- I just think it's like
"give me a green screen and
one of my favorite rock songs,
■f■f
and let's get to work, man."
- The one shot--
- When he goes from
the one leg to the other?
He smoked it.
You got to look, look.
[clamoring]
all: Hey, hey, oh!
- You pay attention to detail.
I did not notice that.
- And you know
he's got bad hips.
- Rob, bad hips!
- Got her.
- Hey, look.
■■ú
I'll just hit her funny bone!
■■■
- ♪ I'm a bad mother[bleep] ♪
♪ I'm an OG ♪
♪ I'm a 60-year-old [bleep] ♪
♪ with a bad knee ♪
■ú■   ♪ I [bleep] ♪
♪ Till I can't see ♪
♪ Everybody trying ♪
♪ To get with me ♪
- No, no!
- If you got a bad knee,
you should not be twerking.
We'll be right back
with more "Ridiculousness."
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ ♪
- Oh!
k ñ■@@@■■■iii■a■a■a■
I know it's hard Maddie.
But I promise,
it's gonna get better.
♪ ♪
(mom giggles)
Where did you go?
When Taco Bell's
Nacho Fries disappear...
...one man must bring them home.
And now you can bring
home Nacho Fries with
a $5 Nacho Fries Box Set.
Now serving at a
Taco Bell near you.
[BONG]
Well, what if I...
drove me home?
[♪♪]
What if we took a leap of faith?
Whoo-hoo!
What if you...
missed my flight next week?
[♪♪]
The All-New RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
♪♪
Your toothpaste may taste fresh,
The All-New RAV4.
but is it removing
enough harmful plaque
that can lead to
tooth decay and gum disease?
Try Arm & Hammer Complete Care.
Only Arm & Hammer contains
50% natural baking soda
which neutralizes acid to
protect enamel.
The foaming formula
penetrates hard to reach areas
to help disrupt plaque build up.
And is proven to remove
up to 5X more plaque
than a regular toothpaste.
For a deep cleaning toothpaste
you can actually feel working,
Try Arm & Hammer Complete Care.
This has been Medifacts
for Arm & Hammer.
♪
Congrats, Kim!
You got your own car,
with your own insurance.
No more driving
that old hand-me-down.
Did you trade it in?
My parents handed it
down to my little brother.
You ready?
Yeah
■
SURPRISE!?
No. Not Beige Betty!
You guys can't
do this to me, seriously?!
My car is like
a rite of passage.
How do you expect
me to drive this?!
Just turn the key...
and yeah, it's just uh...
Some of this...
...it's automatic...
...dual cupholders.
Go with the one that's
here to help life go right.
State Farm.
Kick off the new year
with the new iPhone XR included
for just 40 bucks.
Only from T-Mobile.
It's perfect for all those new
year, new you selfies.
So bring your family to T-Mobile
and get the amazing iPhone
XR included
for just $40 per line.
♪
Oats have a soluble fiber
called beta-glucan,
which can help lower cholesterol
when part of a
heart-healthy diet.
What's more, these oats
have no artificial flavors,
preservatives or added colors.
Now that's something
to celebrate.
[Devo's "Uncontrollable Urge"]
[cheers and applause]
■lcom "Ridiculousness."
Give it up for our guest,
Terrence J.
[cheers and applause]
Okay, Terrence,
do you collect sneakers?
- Yes, I do.
- Where does
the sneaker passion come from,
and how many pairs do you own?
- Oh, if I get,
like, a new pair,
I'll try to give away
an old pair,
so I don't really
keep up with the number.
But I love, like, old sneakers.
Like, this is
a pair of Yeezy 1's.
- Damn.
- This pair, I've had
for over ten years.
Because I couldn't afford them
growing up.
So as soon as I got,
like, on TV,
it was like, always something
really special for me to get.
Like, you know?
- I feel you.
- All-all these sneakers
that I couldn't get.
- Shoes are amazing,
but sometimes,
they're really funny
when you take a slam
and they go sailing off
into nowhere.
- Yes, it is.
- Just like everybody
in this category
we call Fly Kicks.
[cheers and applause]
in this category
we call Fly Kicks.
[upbeat music]
- ♪ Cruising, got my Vans on ♪
♪ Skating ♪
Later!
[groaning]
- Oh, man.
- Whoa!
- Damn, had everybody like
"he's ■■■
■@■ñ■ñ■n■>■N■8■■■x■■■■■■■■■■■■■■
Like--
- He did.
- Literally--
- Yay!
[laughter]
[upbeat music]
- Karate kick!
Gone.
Okay, get rid of that.
All right, let's get to work.
I'ma show you
how to stomp somebody out.
Like, hi-ya!
Oh, God.
- Bruh, he's never
landed that kick
one time in his life.
- No, no.
- He watched one
Bruce Lee movie.
[laughter]
- It was there.
- Oh, man.
- Oh, yeah.
Keep your sandals on, Jerry.
[groaning]
Oh, somebody caught that shoe
to the face.
[laughter]
[upbeat music]
[groaning]
- I'm good!
- Lay down, lay down.
- We're good, we're good.
I ain't got no shoes on,
but I'm good.
- Oh, my God.
- Why the [bleep]
would you try this?
- Because the idea
was probably to do it
like, right next to it,
and the homie
in the rose gold TT
doesn't know how to drive.
- Oh, mys.
- Man.
- No, we're good.
- Oh, my God.
- Anybody see my Jordans?
[laughter]
Just trying to pull out.
[groaning]
- Where did he come from?
- Man.
- Whoa.
- Just decided to
drive into the trash cans.
- The driver didn't even
try to help him.
The driver ran out.
[computer beeps]
He just bounced, bro.
- Yeah, yeah.
- He, just bounced
on him, brother.
- When a random motorcycle guy
hits you and you run,
you got drugs in the trunk.
[laughter]
All right, that is it
for our show today.
Thank you so much
to Terrence J.