This is an adventure.
♪ ♪
This is the memory.
Live in the moment.
Don't get old.
Don't judg
because you can't be free
if you judge people.
♪ ♪
>> [laughs]
>> Love now,
08.
[crowd chanting]
Inspire...
[cheers, whistles, and applause]
[blowing raspberries]
[laughter]
[clucks]
>> All right, that is it for our
show today.
Thank you to our guest,
Bubba Wallace.
For Steelo Brim and Chanel
West Coast, I'm Rob Dyrdek.
We'@@■@@@@@■■@@@@@■
on "Ridiculousness."
■s and applause]
>> ♪ Yeah yeah yeah yeah ♪
♪ ♪
[all shouting]
♪ ♪÷7mm
>> [laughs]
>> both: Six, seven, eight...
>> [clucks]■7
[indistinct chatter]
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, YOU MISSED
YOUR CHANCE.
[shouts]
's Uncontrollable Urge]
♪ ♪ó
>> OH!
>> ♪ YEAH, YEA YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
>> [s]
[cheers and appl■u
>> WELCOME TO RIDICULOUSNESS.d■.
WITH ME, AS ALWAYS, STEELO BRIM
AND CHANEL WEST COAST.
ALL RIGHT, OUR GUEST TODAY
IS A PROFESSIONAL SNOWBOARDER,
BUT MORE THAN ANYTHING, HE
REPRESENTED OUR COUNTRY AND WON
A GOLD MEDAL.
THE ONE AND ONLY
SAGE KOTSENBURG.
[cheers and applause]
WELCOME, MAN. WELCOME.
>> YES. THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
HOW'S IT GOING?
>> HI. NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> SAGE.
WHAT'S UP, MY MAN?
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> WHAT'S GOING DOWN?
>> SAGE, THE LIFE OF A PRO
SNOWBOARDER, WHAT'S IT ALL
ABOUT, MAN?
>> UH...YEAH, SNOWBOARD IN THE
WINTER, AND THEN YOU PRETTY MUCH
DO NOTHING IN THE SUMMER.
YOU JUST HANG OUT.
IT'S PRETTY SICK.
IT'S A GOOD LIFE.
>> OKAY, LET ME ASK YOU
THIS, MAN:
THIS WINTER, WINNING A GOLD
MEDAL, HOW WAS IT, MAN?
>> IT WAS CRAZY.
IT'S LIKE SOMETHING THAT,
I MEAN, YOU ALWAYS WANT TO DO,
BUT, LIKE, WHEN IT HAPPENS,
YOU JUST--IT JUST DOESN'T SEEM
REAL, YOU KNOW?
>> DO YOU ROLL AROUND WITH THE
MEDAL, LIKE, "WHAT'S UP, GIRLS'E
THE RIBBON ON IT WITH JUST A
GOLD CHAIN AND JUST ROCK IT
AROUND, I THINK.
>> LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT SAGE'S
SLOPESTYLE SNOWBOARDING.
>> GIVE ME THAT.
[rock music]
♪ ♪
>> GOING, GOING, GOING, GOING.
GOING.
GET IT. GET IT!
[cheers and applause]
WHOO!
YOU'RE A CHAMPION.
THIS CATEGORY IS FILLED WITHWILE
CHAMPIONS, CALLED
"TOTALLY SLOPELESS."
>> OH, MY GOD.■d
>> NOTHING LIKE A BEAUTIFUL DAY
ON CHIROPRACTIC MOUNTAIN.
>> ♪ TURN DOWN FOR WHAT? ♪
>> Y
AH! AH!
>> ♪ TURN DOWN FOR WHAT? ♪
>> OH, YEAH.
>> OH!
>> WHY IS HE DRESSED LIKE
DALMATIAN, THOUGH, LIKE--
>> I THINK ANYTHING GOES ON THE
HILL, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> ANYTHING GOES.
>> BACKYARD SNOWBOARDING, OH!
>> Fc
>> IN A BACKYARD WITH HARDLYANYN
I'M-GONNA-BE-A-PRO SNOW PATH,
AND THEN YOU JUST DON'T LAUNCH.
>> OH! AH!
■■÷■■÷■v■■÷■
YOUR BUTT JUST ENDS UP IN THE
AIR LIKE THIS.
>> ♪ TURN DOWN FOR WHAT? ♪
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THIS
IS, EITHER.
AY! OH!
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S
REGULATION SIZE, MAN.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S
REGULATION SIZE.
>> I DON'T THINK IT IS, MAN.
AND THEN, WHAT WAS HE DOING,
LAUNCHING OVER TO THIS ONE?
AND HE JUST--NO? OH!
>> PIECE OF HIS LIFE JUST WENT
AWAY RIGHT THERE.
>> I...DON'T...CARE!
>> ♪ TURN DOWN FOR WHAT? ♪
>> OH!
YOU CALL THAT A TOMAHAWK OR
AKA YOUR BOY "TOMMY HAWK."
[laughter]
>> ♪ TURN DOWN FOR WHAT? ♪
>> I'M LESS OF A SNOWBOARD GUY
AND MORE OF AN AVALANCHE GUY.
>> OH! THERE GOES THE FEMUR.
>> OH, MY GOD, HE JUST
KEEPS GOING.
>> OH, MY--
>> HE'S GOOD. HE'S GOOD.
OH! HE'S GOOD.
>> AT NO POINT DID IT EVER LOOK
LIKE HE WAS GOOD ENOUGH TO
DO THIS.
HE WAS LIKE, "NAH, PUT A HELMET
ON ME.
OF COURSE I CAN DO THIS."
WHAT DO WE CALL THIS?
>> YOU CALL THIS A BAD IDEA, IS
WHAT YOU CALL IT.
>> ALL RIGHT, SAGE, WHEN YOU
WERE IN RUSSIA FOR THE GAMES,
RIGHT, I HEARD, LIKE, ALL OF
SOCHI WAS JUST A MESS, LIKE
HOTELS WITH NO RUNNING WATER,
RATS AND SNAKES ALL UP IN BEDS.
HOW WAS IT OUT THERE?
>> UH, I HAD A PRETTY GOOD
EXPERIENCE, OBVIOUSLY, BUT, UM,
THERE WAS, UH, THE COUPLE DOORS
DOWN FROM ME, THERE WAS A
BOBSLEDDER GUY WHO GOT LOCKED IN
HIS BATHROOM, JUST PUNCHED A
HOLE IN THE DOOR AND CRAWLED
THROUGH IT.
>> WHY, 'CAUSE HE GOT
LOCKED INSIDE?
>> HE GOT LOCKED IN THE BATHROOM
AND RAMPAGE JACKSON, JUST, BOOM.
>> WELL, THIS CATEGORY IS
DEDICATED TO RUSSIA, HORRIBLE
LOCATION TO HAVE THE WORLD'S
GREATEST GAMES.w■w■
USELESS CAR!
>> THAT'S WHEN YOU'RE JUST
WAITING ON SOMEBODY TO TOUCH
YOUR [bleep].
YOU KNOW IT'S ALREADY BROKE.
"WATCH, HE GONNA TOUCH IT."
>> YOU BLAME IT ON THEM.
>> "YOU GOT TO PAY FOR IT, BRO!"
>> "OH, YOU--YOU BUYING MY WHOLE
[bleep] NOW!"
[Russian accent] CHECK OUT
THESE RIMS, DOG.
IT STILL WORKS IN RUSSIA!
IT STILL WORKS!
AH, WHO WANTS TO GO
TO BATHROOM?
>> IS THAT A PORTA-POTTY?
>> 'CAUSE I APPRECIATE IT,
'CAUSE I GOT TO [bleep] IN
TRAFFIC ALL THE TIME.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY.
THAT WAS JUST--
>> RUSSIAN OLYMPIC TRAINING.
>> JUMP-STARTING A TRAIN?
NO!
>> AND STAY OUT!
HONEY, DID YOU PACK
THE EXPLOSIVES?
>> OH!
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> MAN, LET'S GET RID OF THIS
BUILDING RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT?
>> OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
THIS IS, LIKE, BUDGET-ASS
DEMOLITION COMPANIES, LIKE, YO--
BLEW IT UP THE FIRST TIME AND
JUST CAUGHT THIS SIDE AND WAS
LIKE, "NO, NO, NO, NO, NO"...
>> JUST LET IT GO.
>> "WE'RE GOOD, NEXT EXPLOSION,
SHE LAYS DOWN."
LIKE, AND THEN INSTEAD OF
COLLAPSING, THE [bleep] ROLLS
OVER INTO SOMEONE ELSE'S
PROPERTY, AND IT'S NO LONGER
THEIR PROBLEM.
IF YOU'RE GONNA END UP IN RUSSIA
AND YOU WANT TO DEMO A BUILDING,
IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH
MORE RIDICULOUSNESS.
[Devo's Uncontrollable Urge]
♪ ♪
>> ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
@@■■@ó
Ordinary tissues left Dakota's
nose sore and red.
So Dad slayed the problem with
Puffs Plus Lotion, instead.
With lotion to soothe and
softness to please.
A nose in need deserves
Puffs, indeed.
Announcer: 7:35 remaining...
Tatum, with the drive...
( ♪♪ )
...and slams it down!
Gatorade studies
the best athletes
to create the most advanced
range of sports fuel.
Gatorade. You fuel us.
We fuel you.
zvzd
to create the most advanced
range of sports fuel.
♪♪
A lot happens in a day.
Outlast happens once.
Outlast all day lip color
with 24 hour stay power.
Now in custom nudes.
From COVERGIRL.
If only there was a place nearby
you could get one of these.
Or these.
Good thing they're
sold literally
everywhere business is done.
I'm pretty sure you could
buy them at a bank.
Not Sorry.
[cheers and applause]
>> WELCOME BACK
TO RIDICULOUSNESS.
WE'RE HERE WITH SAGE KOTSENBURG.
[cheers and applause]
ALL RIGHT, SAGE, THIS NEXT
CATEGORY IS BASICALLY DEDICATED
TO YOUR STYLE, RIGHT?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ONLY IT'S WHAT YOU LOOKED
LIKE AS A SMALL CHILD.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THIS PHOTO.
>> LET'S CHECK THIS OUT.
>> IT'S ALMOST IDENTICAL TO
RIGHT NOW.
HAVE YOU JUST ALWAYS HAD
GLORIOUS, LONG, BLOND LOCKS?
>> JUST GOT THOSE BLOND LOCKS.
THAT WAS ACTUALLY WHERE I JUST
GOT COLLARBONE SURGERY THAT DAY.
>> WHERE DID THAT COME FROM?
>> JUST HOOKED AN EDGE AND JUST
SNAPPED IT.
>> SNAPPED IT UP, RIGHT?
>> SNAPPED IT.
>> WELL, DEDICATED ON YOUR
WILLINGNESS TO GET BACK UP AND
TAKE ON SNOWBOARDING AND
EVENTUALLY TAKE IT TO THE
HIGHEST LEVEL...
"LOCKS OF COURAGE."
CKS OF COURAGE.
>> PROTECT ME, GOLDEN HELMET!
WHAT DO WE GOT?
>> OH!
THERE GOES HIS COLLARBONE.
>> WHAT THE [bleep] IS
THIS, MAN?
IS THAT AN IPAD?
>> IT'S GOT TO BE AN IPAD.
>> THIS MOTHER[bleep] TRIES TO
SLIDE A RAIL--
THIS IS CRAZY, BUT--
>> OH!
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE IN A SCOOTER
CREW, YOU DESERVE THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> HWAH!
>> [crying]
>> OH, THERE'S THE TAILBONE.
>> OW, MY [bleep] ASS!
OW, MY [bleep] ASS!
■÷■÷■÷ç÷■÷■÷
>> MY NECK, MY FACE, BUT NOT
MY BOARD!
>> OH.
>> YOUR FACE IS HALF GONE, AND
ALL YOU CARE ABOUT IS THE
SKATEBOARD GETTING WET?
>> YEAH.
>> COMING IN HOT.■■>■ O
>> YEAH--AH!
>> OH, MY GOD.
H!
>> IF YOU GO BACK, THOUGH, IT
LOOKED LIKE AN EXORCISM, LIKE,
LOOK AT HIM.
>> YOU KNOW, THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT--[laughs]
>> LIKE IT'S A DEMON COMING OUT
OF THERE.
[laughter]
>> I CAN TELL YOU, WHEN YOU GET
A SKATEBOARD, LIKE, DEEP IN YOUR
ASS[bleep]--
>> NO.
>> OOH.
>> IT FEELS LIKE THE DEVIL COMES
OUT OF YOU.
ALL RIGHT, SAGE, WE GOT THIS
FAMILY PHOTO I'D LIKE TO PUT UP
REAL QUICK, ALL RIGHT?
>> ALL RIGHT, YEP.
[laughs]
ME ON THE RIGHT.
>> WAIT, THAT'S YOU ON
THE RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> I'D LIKE TO GO DOWN, I'D LIKE
TO NAME EACH PERSON.
IF YOU COULD NAME--I'M GONNA
POINT 'EM OUT, AND YOU NAME 'EM.
>> OKAY, YEAH.
SAGE.
MY BROTHER BLAZE.
MY SISTER KIRRA.
JEREMY.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
HERE'S BROTHER JEREMY. OKAY.
>> YEAH, THE BOSS.
>> SO WHAT'S YOUR BROTHER AND
SISTER DO?
>> UH, THEY BOTH SNOWBOARD TOO.
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT A
FULL-FLEDGED, AMAZING
SNOWBOARDING FAMILY.
NOW WHAT'S JEREMY DO?
>> HE TOOK A DIFFERENT ROUTE.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, HE TOOK A
DIFFUTE.
DEDICATED TO THE BROTHER THAT
KIND OF STICKS OUT IN THE CREW--
>> STEEZY.
>> OUR CATEGORY CALLED
"JEREMYS."
TAKE A LOOK.
>> JEREMYS.
>> T, MAN.
MAN, ALL RIGHT.
SAGE!
BLAZE!
JEREMY.
[all laughing]
>> HOLY--
>> I CAN'T. I CAN'T, MAN.
I CAN'T. GO, GO, GO, MAN.
AW, YEAH!
SAGE!
BLAZE!
COME ON, JEREMY!
>> OH!
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET FOR
SKIING, YOU KNOW?■J■÷■■■■>■■■■>■
■■■■■■'■
>> HOLY--
>> SAGE! AW, YEAH.
>> BLAZE!WE GO.
YEAH!■''
BRING HO DOESN'T
HAVE A TROPHY.
>> OH!
>> MAN, I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT WE
FOUND THIS MANY VIDEOS OF THE--
OF JEREMY SLAMMING.
SAGE!
>> OH, HE MADE IT.
HE ACED IT.
>> BLAZE!
HERE'S ME!
YOU DON'T WANT TO END UP THE
JEREMY IN YOUR FAMILY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH
MORE RIDICULOUSNESS.
>> ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
>> YOU GOT FOUR TEETH PULLED.
>> WHAT?
ó■aD2ó
"WOW"
"WHAT A NICE PLACE"
♪♪■O■O■O■■ç@ç@■@@
Kick off the new year
with the new iPhone XR included
for just 40 bucks.
Only from T-Mobile.
It's perfect for all those new
year, new you selfies.
So bring your family to T-Mobile
and get the amazing iPhone
XR included
for just $40 per line.
■@■@■@■@E÷)&■&
Mhm
Aaaah!
Nooooo...
Quick, the Quicker Picker Upper!
Bounty picks up messes quicker
and is 2x more absorbent than
the leading ordinary brand.
[Son loudly clears throat]
Sigh
[Mom and dad laugh]
Bounty, the Quicker Picker
Upper.
At Suave, we don't believe in
faking h hair,
[record scratch]
with fancy extensions.
We skip the tricks and deliver
real results...
...and infuse real ingredients..
...like Suave Coconut Oil
Infusion with Pure Coconut Oil.
These results don't lie.
Suave.
For hair you can believe.
0 ■■■■■
Not much here,
except the usual.
What i■vce
things up a bit?
Alexa...
"Fire"
by The Ohio Players
♪Fire (uh) (uh)♪
What if we turn it up a notch?
♪Fire (It's all about) (Uh, uh)♪
What if we go off the map?
♪Fire (Woo, woo, woo)♪
♪Fire♪
The all-new RAV4.
Toyota.
Let's go places.
[cheers and applause]
>> WELCOME BACK
TO RIDICULOUSNESSB,■■'RE HERE W$
[cheers and applause]
SAGE, WE HAVE SOME VIDEO
FOOTAGE WHERE IT LOOKS LIKE YOU
MIGHT BE REALLY, REALLY HIGH.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, I'M TALKING--
WE'RE TALKING FULL-FLEDGED,
FULL-SCALE HIGH ON DRUGS.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT IT.
>> ALL RIGHT, GOD.
MY TONGUE, MY MOUTH.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE READY.
>> SPARTACUS.
"I'M GONNA WATCH SPARTACUS."
>> I'M GONNA WATCH SPARTACUS
ALL DAY!
>> OH, MAN.
>> SO DID YOU EVER END UP
RUNNING THAT MARATHON?
>> I DIDN'T, ACTUALLY.
>> HAVE YOU EVER RAN A MARATHON
IN YOUR LIFE?
>> I'M JUST--IT'S NOT MY STYLE.
IT'S NOT MY STYLE.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, DEDICATED TO
YOU BEING HIGH AND JUST SORT OF
CHATTERING AWAY, THE CATEGORY:
"CHATTER GAS."
>> YESBEST
>> MOO-MOO.■%■%
YOU'RE MAKING YOURSELF MORE IN
PAIN BY CRYING AND MOVING
YOUR MOUTH.
YOU JUST--
YOUR GAUZE IS COMING OUT.
STOP!
OKAY, CALM DOWN.
>> SO SAD.
>> VICTOR, YOU'RE GONNA MESS
YOUR TEETH UP.
YOU GOT FOUR TEETH PULLED.
WHY WOULD--
>> YOU NEED TO GO TO SLEEP.
>> THAT PURPLE MONSTER?
WHAT MONSTER?
WHAT?
>> YES.
>> DID YOU HAVE YOUR WISDOM
TEETH OUT?
>> [laughs] WHAT?
>> YOU'RE NOT A NASCAR DRIVER.
>> SORRY.
>> LOOK AT ME.
>> BUT I AM!
>> SHE'S KILLING HER DREAMS.
>> SHE LITERALLY KILLED THE POOR
GIRL'S DREAMS.
>> EAT THE CRACKER.
>> "WHO ARE YOU?"
>> WHAT?
>> YES.
>> THIS COULD HAVE GONE
ANY DIRECTION.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT COULD HAVE BEEN LIKE, "YEAH,"
LIKE, "HOLY [bleep], YOU FINE,"
OR, "WHAT THE [bleep]?
I MARRIED THAT?"
>> WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
>> I KNOW, WE'RE GONNA GET YOU
ANOTHER ONE WHEN WE GET HOME.
>> OKAY.
>> AW!
>> TEAMWORK!
>> THAT IS LOVE.
THAT IS LOVE.
>> THAT'S LOVE RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S AMAZING.
>> ALL RIGHT, SAGE, WHEN YOU
MADE THE FINALS, TO HAVE A SHOT
AT WINNING AN OLYMPIC GOLD
MEDAL, YOU RANG OUT A TWEET TO
THE WORLD TO LET THEM KNOW, AND
THIS IS HOW IT CAME OUT:
NOW, YOU'RE WORKING YOUR WHOLE
LIFE, YOU'RE ONE OF THE BEST
SLOPESTYLE RIDERS IN THE
WORLD--THAT'S NOT RANDOM.
>> IT FELT RANDOM.
>> IT DID--YOU WERE LIKE, "MAN,
I CAN'T BELIEVE I MADE THIS
FINAL.
I MAKE EVERY FINAL."
WE'D LIKE TO SHOW YOU WHAT
RANDOM REALLY IS.
>> YEAH.
>> THE CY: "HOW RANDOM."
TAKE A LOOK.
JUST MARRIED!
>> WHAT?
>> I LOVE THIS, MAN.
I LOVE ALL THINGS RANDOM, BUT
THERE'S NOTHING I ENJOY MORE
THAN A GOAT BACKPACK.
WHOA. HOW RANDOM IS THIS?
>> OH, MY GOD.
RANDOM AS [bleep].
>> OH.
>> THIS IS SOME FREAKY [bleep]
RIGHT HERE.
LIKE, CAN YOU IMAGINE HER
BOYFRIEND, LIKE, "I ALWAYS
WANTED TO [bleep] A UNICORN."
>> THAT IS SKETCHY.
>> AH, YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT'S SKETCHY?
WE'LL GO BACK.
>> THAT THERE'S PEOPLE OUT THERE
LIKE THAT.
>> YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT'S SKETCHY?
I'M GUESSING THEF
THIS UNICORN--
>> EW!
>> TOO FAR!
LIKE, WHAT?
>> I'M TEDDY DEATHSPIN.
WILL YOU PLAY WITH ME?
>> OH!
>> THAT IS SO SCARY.
>> WHO MADE THAT TOY?
>> I THINK IT'S KIND OF
CUTE, MAN.
[farting and flute notes]
>> HOLY--
>> HERE'S THE THING--
>> I DON'T WANT TO GO BACK.
>> I DON'T EITHER.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING BACK.
WE'RE NOT GOING BACK.
IT'S LIKE, THIS MORNING, THIS
VIDEO POPPED UP, AND IT WAS TOO
EARLY TO DECIDE, LIKE, "MAN, IS
THAT TOO WEIRD?
IS THAT JUST WHEN RANDOM GOES A
STEP TOO FAR...
WITH THE FART FLUTE?"
AND I THINK YES.
>> FINAL CALL FOR PASSENGERS OF
AIR FRANCE AND--
>> JUST CRUISING.
>> POSSIBLY THE GREATEST
THING I'VE EVER SEEN.
THE GREATEST THING I'VE
EVER SEEN.
THAT'S WHEN YOUR FLIGHT'S
DELAYED WAY TOO LONG.
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHEN YOU'VE HAD
A COUPLE TOO MANY DELAYS.
>> THIS IS LIKE ONE OF THOSE
TIMES WHERE YOU TOOK, LIKE,
SLEEPING PILLS, AND YOU WERE
STILL DRUNK, AND ALL FOUR OF YOU
ARE BLACKED OUT.
IF YOU GET BORED AT AN AIRPORT,
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT TO DO:
KEEP IT RANDOM.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK WITH
MORE RIDICULOUSNESS.
>> ♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH ♪
>> AAH!
■■■=■=■=■=■■■■■■i■■■■■x■;
Could switching to GEICO really
save you fifteen percent or more
on car insurance?
Did the little piggy
cry wee wee wee
all the way home?
Weeeeeeeee!
We we weeeee!
Weeeeeeee!
Max.
MAXWELL!
Yeah?
You're home.
Oh, cool.
Thanks Mrs. A.
GEICO.
Fifteen minutes could save
you fifteen percent or more.
♪
And for me there's only one
winner. Crunch.;l■■■;■e
embracing the lightness
of crispy rice.
Crunch. The chocolate bar
all Americans love.
My gums are irritated.
I don't have to worry about
that, do I?
Actually, you do.
Harmful bacteria lurk just below
the gum line.
New Crest Gum Detoxify works
below the gum line
to neutralize harmful plaque
bacteria
and help reverse early gum
damage.
Gum Detoxify, from Crest.
Rise to Grapeness.
You can Duo anything.
>> DON'GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF RIDICULOUSNESS
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
[cheers and applause]
WELCOME BACK TO RIDICULOUSNESS.
WE'RE WITH SAGE KOTSENBURG.
[cheers and applause]
OKAY, SAGE.
HOW MANY HOURS UPON HOURS UPON
HOURS UPON HOURS OF GOPRO
FOOTAGE DO YOU HAVE?
>> I HAVE A LOT.
I USUALLY JUST LEAVE THAT THING
RUNNING ALL DAY.
>> WHAT DO YOU DO WITH ALL THAT?
OR DO YOU GET IT, FILM IT, AND
JUST HAND IT OFF TO SOMEBODY?
>> UH, I TRY EDITING IT MYSELF,
BUT I DEFINITELY SEND IT TO
THEM, 'CAUSE THEY DO IT WAY
BETTER THAN ME.
WHOO!
>> YEAH!
>> WHEN GOPRO FOOTAGE IS DONE
THE RIGHT WAY BY PROFESSIONALS,
IT'S INCREDIBLE.
WHEN IT'S DONE BY PEOPLE THAT
HAVE NO BUSINESS DOING ANYTHING
OTHER THAN SLAMMING, WE CALL
THAT A "NO-PRO."
TAKE A LOOK.
WHEN I ANALYZE T■
LATER, I'LL KNOW NEVER TO DO
THIS AGAIN.
>> ♪ LET ME TAKE A SELFI■
>> HERE WE GO. HIGH SPEED, MAN.
I'M IN SOME WEIRD RACE--
I'M ON THE■/■/
I'M ON MY FACE.
>> OH!
>> WHIPPING AROUND.
WHIPPING AROUND.
OH, I'M DOWN. YOU'RE DOWN.
>> AAH!
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I'M'
>> I'M GOOD.
>> ♪ LET ME TAKE A SELFIE ♪
>> IS THAT A MUPPET RIDING
WITH HIM?
LIKE, WHAT HAND IS THAT
RIGHT THERE?
LOOKED LIKE A MUPPET AT
THE WINDOW.
>> THEY LOOK LIKE
MICKEY'S HANDS.
>> RIGHT, LEFT, LEFT, RIGHT,
RIGHT, STRAIGHT, LEFT.
AH, [bleep].
>> OH. WATCH OUT!
>> OH!
>> OH! WOW.
>> THEY JUST MISSED HIM.
>> YEAH, GO BACK.
THAT'S THAT BAD SURVIVAL
INSTINCT GUY.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS
COMPLETELY FREE.
HE PANICS AND DROPS.
>> OH!
>> ♪ I GUESS I TOOK ♪
♪ A GOOD SELFIE ♪
THIS IS A SICK IDEA.
>> WHOLE LOT OF LEATHER.
>> THERE WE GO.
>> OH.
OH!
OH, BOY.
>> [screaming]
>> OH!
>> YOU INSTANTANEOUSLY KNOW
EVERYTHING'S GOING BAD
RIGHT NOW.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> [screaming]
>> THAT SCREAM OF HIS.
>> I JUST POV'D MY PANTS.
OKAY, OKAY.
THERE YOU HAVE IT: NO-PROS.
>> NO-PRO.
AMAZING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE AT THE END OF THE EPISODE
WHERE WE LIKE TO THROW UP A
HASHTAG AND TRY TO GUESS AT
MAYBE WHAT THE VIDEO COULD BE.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT WHAT
WE GOT.
>> [laughs] MIDDLEFOOT?
>> #MIDDLEFOOT.
CHANEL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> [laughs] I HAVE A DIRTY MIND.
I DON'T WANT TO SAY WHAT
I THINK.
>> SAGE, MIDDLEFOOT, MAN!HAT'S .
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S THAT THI■
>> THAT'S ALL I COULD THINK
ABOUT IS THIRD LEG.
>> OKAY, WELL, LET'S TAKE A LOOK
AT WHAT WE'VE DECIDED TO HASHTAG
"MIDDLEFOOT."
>> [speaking French]■a
>> IT'S FRENCH, AND OUT HERE--
UH-OH.
>> OH, NO.
>> THE CAMERAMAN HAD TO DO A
WIDE SHOT!
>> WOW.
BUT UNDERSTAND THIS, THOUGH.
YOU KNOW WHEN A JOKE REALLY
DOESN'T WORK, GHT?
SO THEN HE'S LIKE, OH, MY--MY--
MY--MY [bleep].
AND THEN SHE'S LIKE, "NO,"
AND HE'S LIKE,
"OH, WELL, SORRY, EH."
>> NEVER MIND.
THAT'S SOMEONE'S, LIKE, GRANDPA,
YOU KNOW?
>> OH YEAH.
AKA GRANDPA MIDDLEFOOT.
THAT IS IT FOR OUR SHOW.
THANK YOU, SAGE KOTSENBURG.
FOR STEELO BRIM
AND CHANEL WEST COAST,