[door opens]
See what dirt
you can find on her.
Joy.
You have a visitor.
A Mr. Martin Mariner.
Just your type.
Are you Frank Hathaway?
-Are you American?
-Yes, sir.
From Nashville, Tennessee.
So, are you Frank Hathaway?
Uh, yes.
Oh. Oh, Frank!
-[grunts]
-It's so great
to finally meet you.
Or should I call you
Francis?
Oh, let me take
a look at you.
You have two seconds
to let me go.
Oh, no way. I've been dreaming
about this moment for years.
One... two...
-Frank...
-Easy, tiger.
-I did warn him.
-Too much.
Frank, please.
That hurts.
A lot.
Who the hell are you?
I'm your uncle.
What?
We're family, Frank.
Ain't it wonderful?
[Frank]
What, you're my dad's brother?
[Martin]
That's right.
My mother is your
grandmother.
But don't you think my dad
might have mentioned you?
He might not even know
I exist.
I was adopted at birth.
I was raised by a wonderful
British couple
who moved out
to Tennessee.
But now they've both passed,
I'm tracing my blood relations.
And you, Frank...
[clicks tongue]
...you are my first
discovery.
Cobblers.
Well, I'll show you.
Now, birth certificate.
And that's my mother.
[Lu]
"Elizabeth Hathaway."
Is that your grandmother?
Well, it's a common name.
[Lu]
Maiden name: Foster.
I haven't got a clue
about maiden names.
She died years
before I was born.
How come the father's
not listed?
Well, young man, it's very
possible that I'm a love child.
Oh, great.
So now you're calling my nana
a tramp as well as a liar.
Here's our family tree, Frank.
I only managed to go back
to the 17th century.
[Sebastian]
Incredible.
So, 1953.
Is that when
your nan died?
Well, around that time, yes.
I can't find Elizabeth's
death certificate
to confirm
the actual day.
But since I know that my mother
died in childbirth,
got to be my birthday:
4th of July, Independence Day.
That's great detective work,
Martin, yeah.
-Thank you, ma'am.
-[Frank] Ah!
She died in childbirth,
did you say?
That's right.
Because my nana died
in a car crash.
Are you absolutely certain
about that, Frank?
Because my adoptive parents
were told that my mother died
giving birth to me.
It's the only thing about
my nana that I am sure of.
Ow, Frank!
[Frank]
Wrong Elizabeth Hathaway.
Oh, what a shame. There we are.
Let me help you with these.
-Frank...
-Come on.
[Martin] We're related, Frank.
I can feel it.
[Frank]
Apparently not.
At least let me buy you
a coffee.
Come on.
[in mock American accent]
Thanks for stopping by!
What?
He was obviously
a con man.
What's he after, then?
Your fortune?
[sighs]
So, when did this Lola
start work here?
[Leon]
Three months ago.
I gave her the job.
I honestly thought
I could trust her.
That's what hurts
the most.
-Aye. When was this accident?
-[Leon] A month ago.
I found Lola out in the back,
screaming.
She claimed a box
of Shakespeare busts
had fallen off a trolley
and landed on her foot.
-[chuckles]
-[Diana] Next thing we know
she's on crutches and suing us
for compensation.
No witnesses,
I take it?
[Leon]
Of course not.
[Lu]
Twisted ankle ligaments.
The only thing twisted
is that girl's morality.
So you want us to prove
she was faking the injury?
Photos, videos.
You do whatever it takes.
Surveillance isn't cheap.
And neither are
compensation payouts.
-Fair enough.
-The awful thing is
the hearing's been
brought forward.
It's now next week.
We will get on this
right away.
Don't worry.
[Frank]
I think you put a few too many
noughts on there by mistake.
[laughs]
Frank.
Yeah. Just...
[Lu sighs]
[Lu]
He seemed credible.
[Frank]
My nan died in a car crash.
What if they lied to you?
That happens a lot
in family.
I'm not related
to that nutter.
Oh, hello.
So far, so convincing.
Now?
[sighs]
This seat taken?
-Go ahead.
-Oh, thanks.
Do you mind if I...?
They're a right pain,
those things, aren't they?
-Yeah, I'm sick of them.
-Yeah.
No, I broke my toe
last year.
Fell down the stairs.
I was off my head.
It was totally my fault.
Twisted ligaments.
Oh, right.
-How?
-This box fell on my foot.
Oh, ouch.
[laughs]
Was that at home?
Work.
Oh, well, I hope you get
plenty of sympathy for it.
Not exactly.
No? What do you mean?
Well, my bosses thought
I was lying, which was nice.
-Didn't even get an apology.
-Oh, honestly.
The things employers
get away with now, hey?
Hello, darling.
Small world.
Oh, I love the new look.
I'm Gloria, Lu's friend.
-Lola.
-We've only just met.
Really?
Okay if I join you?
No, I'm not staying.
What am I doing?
I've got Carlos coming--
oh, in 10 minutes.
My masseur.
Beautiful man,
and surprisingly punctual
for a Brazilian.
Nice to meet you.
See you soon, Lu.
-Bye.
-I should go, too.
-Oh, right. Okay.
Yeah, as soon as we catch
her out, Mr. Tarsich,
I will call you
right away, okay?
I will.
Yeah, bye. Bye.
That is the third time
he's called already today.
It's from Sebastian.
"According to our contact
at the credit check company,
Lola Gower owes over
20,000 in payday loans."
Then she needs
this compensation.
Well, if she's faking it,
she's doing a decent job.
Oh, hello.
He looks pleased
with himself.
[Frank]
I don't believe it.
What?
That Yank.
He's stalking me.
[sighs]
Weirdo.
All you need to do is find out
the date your nan died.
Then if it's not July 4th, 1953,
you're in the clear, aren't you?
[Frank]
How am I going to do that
with Mom and Dad gone?
Sounds like it's a job
for Frank Hathaway.
Frank Hathaway
already has a job.
Watching somebody
watch telly.
Oh, it's going to be
a long night.
[cell phone rings]
Oh! It's him again.
-Again?
-Again.
Hello, Mr. Tarsich.
[Leon, on phone]
Anything?
No, she's still in her flat,
I'm afraid.
She hasn't left since lunchtime.
This is pointless.
Yeah, well,
as I said before, Mr. Tarsich,
patience is the key.
You don't understand.
We're not insured.
Well, not with
the right policy, anyway.
Oh.
I haven't told Diana,
but if that girl wins,
it could cripple us.
-[sighs]
-I see.
It's my fault.
I was halfway through
filling in the form,
but then I had to go away
for work.
[Lu]
Right.
[gasps and giggles]
Oh.
Double bacon, double egg,
double ketchup for the vitamins.
Thank you.
No sign of life?
Mm.
I think we need to step up
our coverage.
Let's see if the clients will
stump up for a hidden camera.
Mm.
-For me?
-Yeah.
Hmm.
Is-- oh.
Cheers, Ajay.
[rattles door]
[distant police siren]
[camera clicks]
[car doors close]
[footsteps]
Oh, look,
it's the marshmallow twins.
-Hi, Frank.
-Hello.
Frank.
Ah, Christina.
Didn't take you
as the gift shop type.
Yeah, I ran out
of Waterlily soap.
[chuckles and clears throat]
Fraud claim involving
an ex-member of staff.
I came to see my client.
Going to have to talk
to the husband now.
And you can scratch her
off the list,
the girl we've been
trailing.
Thanks.
And given it's a robbery
gone wrong...
Is it?
Back door forced.
Signs of a struggle.
Blow to the head
with Arden's finest.
Till open and money gone.
What does that look like
to you?
Yeah.
You see those
pieces of glass?
Mm-hm.
[Frank]
How did they get there?
Embedded themselves
during the struggle.
Yeah, but they're not embedded,
are they?
They've just been placed there.
When that glass fell
on the victim,
she was lying still,
almost certainly dead.
Now, why would the killer add
smashed glass after the murder?
Answer:
to make it look like
a robbery.
You might want to talk
to someone called P.
P?
Yeah, it's the person she texted
at 7 minutes past 3:00
yesterday afternoon.
You tampered
with the victim's phone?
I took a brief look,
and I'm wearing a glove.
[phone beeps]
[Marlowe]
"We need to talk.
"Come and find me
after closing.
"The cat's away.
Kiss, kiss."
The "cat" being the husband,
Leon.
He's not back yet.
I'll call him if you like.
-Save you the trouble.
-Thanks.
I've got it from here, Frank.
Well, just keep
an open mind.
Don't patronize me.
-I wasn't.
-Good.
You can get on with
your fraud claim, then.
Okay. Over here, guys.
It's like Luke Skywalker
telling Yoda to sod off.
Yoda? Really?
[knock on door, door opens]
So it looks like the profits
from the business
all went to Diana,
and Leon just got
a monthly wage.
Not much of one, either.
[Frank] So she's skinning him
for his cash
and cuckolding him
with this "P" character.
Leon Tarsich must be
in the frame, right?
[Sebastian]
Come through, Mr. Tarsich.
We're very sorry
for your loss.
I...
I don't think I'll need...
the Lola thing doesn't seem
like such a...
We understand entirely.
Don't we, Frank?
Of course. Yeah.
-Thank you.
-[Frank] The...
the local police are really
stretched at the moment,
so they've asked us to help
track down Diana's killer.
I'm really sorry
to have to ask this,
but where were you
yesterday?
I was in Manchester.
At a gift shop
conference.
Came back this morning
as soon as I heard the...
And everything was all right
at home, was it?
Yeah, it was good.
[Lu]
Yeah? Diana was happy?
Perfectly.
No suggestion
of another man?
No.
Was there anything else?
No. Thank you.
[Lu]
Thank you.
We'll do everything we can
to help.
Sebastian, find out if there was
a gift shop conference
in Manchester yesterday.
Fine. By the way,
did you notice his nails?
-They were perfect.
-[door opens]
-[door closes]
-Frank.
Now you're a businessman
first and foremost.
-I respect that.
-Yeah, goodbye.
You find out the date
your grandma died,
I'll double it.
Frank.
Giving Marlowe
a free Jedi lesson
isn't going to pay
the bills.
[sighs]
-[Frank] Anything?
-[Sebastian] Mm-mm.
What? There's nothing anywhere
about my nana's death online?
Nope.
-Was she buried?
-Yes.
Well, then the date will be
on the gravestone.
I'll have to find
the cemetery first.
Yeah, but you're
Mr. Family History, aren't you?
All I know is it's in a village
somewhere in the Cotswolds.
The Cotswolds?
Yeah, my granddad travelled
south with work.
I mean, I went there once,
but I was about 11.
[sighs]
Gonna have to resort to using
a Ouija board at this rate.
I need another drink.
What's that?
[Frank]
Looks like blood.
Hey...
If we could get Forrest Gump Sr.
done for something,
we could be off the hook.
I'm going to send one of these
to my mate Freddie at Forensics.
Ooh.
What is it?
Email from the Golden Horizons
Gift Shop Conference
in Manchester.
Apparently, Leon Tarsich
registered yesterday morning,
and guess what?
Afternoon and evening,
never showed up.
Well, I was there.
Did you talk to anyone?
Well, not really.
Look, I've already been through
all this with the police.
Now, we appreciate that,
Mr., uh, Tarshah...
-Sich.
-...ich.
[Lu] I notice from
your bank statements
that you've been making
regular payments
to "Bar MM" on the second Friday
of every month.
The police let you see
my bank statements?
You wouldn't believe
how much they trust us.
Well, that's the Mucky Mallard.
I go there
with a couple of mates.
Hey, I go there every Friday.
Yeah, I thought
I recognized you.
Can I use your
bathroom?
Yeah, it's just on the right
past the bedroom.
So, then, Diana's money?
Must be quite a whack of it.
Does that come to you, is it?
I haven't even
thought about it.
Of course, sorry,
I didn't mean to...
He's never been in the Mucky
Mallard on a Friday night,
I can tell you that much.
[Lu]
And they had separate bedrooms.
[Frank]
So, problems in the sack,
wife playing away,
a clear financial motive,
and an alibi that stinks.
[laughs]
Yeah, I'm with them now,
Mr. Tarsich.
I'll call you back.
Misrepresentation
is a criminal offense, Frank.
So's murder.
-Stop harassing him.
-Only if you promise to start.
I don't know why
you're wasting your time.
He couldn't have killed
his wife anyway.
-Why not?
-He was on the phone to you.
Based on smashed clocks
at the scene,
an aborted 999 call
on the victim's phone
and the pathology report,
we're sure that
the attack took place
at exactly 11 minutes
past 7:00.
-[Frank] Well?
-[Lu] Yeah.
Leon was in the middle of one of
his five-minute rants with me.
Making a business call while
committing a violent murder.
That's some serious
multitasking.
I got a phone call
from Forensics.
You know the blood you found
on those bank notes?
-Yeah?
-It belongs to Diana.
-What?
-So the question is,
where did you get
the cash from?
[cell door opens]
[Marlowe]
Mr. Mariner.
Frank!
Are you two
really related?
-Yes.
-No.
-You've got five minutes.
-Thank you.
Frank, you got to help me.
They're saying
I murdered some woman.
[sighs]
I take it you didn't kill her?
No!
Where'd you get the money?
[sighs]
From a guy.
I met him outside
a pawnbroker's.
What pawnbroker's?
It was called Cash Changers,
something like that.
What? Quid Converters?
That's it.
What were you doing there?
I was selling
my parents' jewellery.
Why?
So I could hire you.
This guy said
that he would pay double
whatever I was offered inside.
And he did.
And that's the money
you gave us?
Mmm.
Right. Listen, Martin.
I need you
to describe this man to me.
A lizard tattoo
on the side of his neck.
It's a start.
You seem pretty keen
to get Martin off the charge.
Well, I just--
I don't think he's guilty.
Is that it?
Yes, that's it.
It's got nothing
to do with the fact
he's my long-lost uncle.
[laughs]
Methinks he doth protest
too much.
[Sebastian clears throat]
Mr. Tarsich.
He's brought your money.
You can count it.
Ah, don't worry.
My solicitor called.
Lola's dropping
the compensation claim.
On compassionate grounds.
-That must be a relief.
-Yeah.
Oh, and I'm sorry for
dropping you in it earlier.
Ah, no hard feelings.
You want to help,
and I appreciate that.
Are you getting
anywhere?
You don't know of any
of your customers or suppliers
who might have, like, a lizard
tattoo on the neck, do you?
Lizard?
No, I don't.
Sorry.
Phil has got a tattoo.
I'm not sure
what it's of, though.
Phil?
Yeah, Phil Layman.
Lola's boyfriend.
Thanks.
I'm on my tea break, mate.
Turning down work, Phil?
You must be doing
all right.
Hey, nice tattoo.
Unusual.
You what? Do I know you?
[Frank]
No, but you know my uncle.
-[Phil] Oh, yeah?
-[Frank] Yeah.
You bought some jewellery
off him outside Quid Converters.
Big American fella.
Cheesy sod.
No, don't know nothing about it.
It's all right, Phil.
Don't worry about it.
I'm here to buy it back.
Family heirloom,
you see.
Yeah, my uncle,
he's a few hot dogs
short of a stand,
if you know what I mean.
[Frank laughs]
Come on, how much
do you want for it?
Hey, as I said,
I don't know nothing about it.
[Frank]
I hear Lola's dropped the claim.
-Do you work out?
-You...
-Who are you?
-[Frank] Who am I?
That's a fundamental question.
Who is anyone?
Who are you?
[grunts]
[Phil]
Tell me who sent you,
or I'll break your arm in two.
[Frank]
You've got a temper on you.
-[bone cracks]
-Ow!
[groaning]
Oh, you brute.
I'm a copper.
Of course you are.
Try me.
[groaning]
Cheers, Phil.
Don't point at me.
[car door closes]
[engine starts]
[grunts]
So, now you know
how Martin felt.
Thanks for the sympathy.
[groans]
Well?
Found this in the glove
compartment.
Ah. Classic burner.
We've found our "P."
Yeah.
[Marlowe] We located
a couple of bank notes
with blood on them
in his flat,
and we also found him
on CCTV
in the vicinity of the gift shop
at the time of the murder.
And he's got previous
for robbery.
How do you know that?
Because some people in here
still rate me.
Never knew you were
so sensitive.
So Diana gets Phil over to tell
him she's ending the affair.
He takes it badly, whacks her
on the head with a big fossil.
And then he staged
a robbery.
Go on then, say it.
I'm not sure it was Phil
who killed her.
What?
Well, according
to the phone,
Diana wasn't his only bit
on the side.
Okay. So?
So why would her ending it
make him so angry?
Frank, I'm out.
[groans]
[whispering]
He's a big fan of yours.
He can't wait to get back
to your search.
Well, every silver lining
has a cloud.
[laughs]
Ah, ah. Come on, walk.
[Frank sighs]
[Gloria] It was when Lu
gave me that look.
[laughs]
That was the moment
I realized I'd walked
into a secret
undercover operation,
and I nearly
had a heart attack.
Well, Lu says you covered it
like Dame Judi herself.
I wasn't that good.
One of my regulars, that is.
[Sebastian]
What, the murderer?
[Gloria]
No. The husband.
I didn't know
his real name.
Poor bloke.
Well, what name
did he use with you?
Linda.
Linda?
[Frank]
How many more parishes to check?
Uh... 103.
[cell phone rings]
Oh.
I've got to take this.
I'll meet you outside.
-Yes?
-Having fun?
-No.
-Family, eh?
Well, I've worked out
where Leon Tarsich
really spent
those Friday nights.
Well, go on.
The Moody Mule.
You're joking.
Which rather begs the question,
did the wife know?
Hang on.
-It's Friday today.
-Exactly.
Second of the month.
-[indistinct chattering]
-[jazzy music playing]
♪ The poet speaks
But no one listens ♪
Hi.
I'm Adele.
Linda.
Can I get another one,
Gina, please?
-Okay.
-You celebrating?
Or drowning your sorrows?
Bit of a week.
Death in the family.
No.
Oh, that's awful.
I'm so sorry.
I lost my dog recently.
Were you very close?
Yeah.
And no.
Thank you.
It was my wife.
Oh, my gosh.
Had she been ill?
Yeah.
Even so.
Poor you.
Part of me feels relieved.
Well, if she'd been ill
for a long time...
It's not that.
She couldn't accept this.
No?
Found out a few months back.
Two weeks later,
she started sleeping
with an employee's
boyfriend.
Unbelievable.
That's not the worst
of it, though.
[Sebastian]
Oh.
From cigarettes?
She burned you?
So, Diana was physically
abusing Leon
because he wasn't the man
she thought she married.
And he knew
about her affair.
I'd have been out of there
like a shot.
He had no money, though.
Yeah, he's got plenty now,
hasn't he?
So that's a double motive
for murder.
Revenge and cash.
Plus a lack of alibi.
Except we know he didn't do it,
because when Diana was killed,
he was on the phone to me.
-We've missed something.
-What?
I don't know,
but we've got to find it.
I'll speak to you later.
[phone beeps off]
So, was he impressed
with my handiwork?
Yes. Very.
He's... yeah.
He didn't say anything,
did he?
That's all right.
I only do this job
for the lavish salary.
-[cell phone rings]
-Oh.
Lola's curtains.
Sorry, what?
Who has a night in by the telly
with the curtains wide open?
Maybe she's
claustrophobic.
Maybe she wanted
to be seen.
By who?
I haven't got that far.
I'll see you later.
Perhaps she's
an exhibitionist.
Well, it wasn't much
of a show.
All she did was get up a couple
of times to get the remote.
What if we were
the audience?
[sighs]
It's all right.
I trust you.
Oh, thanks, Frank.
What do they call
this place?
Oh, uh...
Risley Cross.
I've been here before.
-Gloria.
-Oh!
Oh, sorry. Leon Tarsich,
he hired woman's clothes
from you, is that right?
All the time.
Dresses. Hats. Shoes.
-Wigs?
-Of course.
He borrowed one
last week.
Which one?
Oh...
[sighs]
Did he ask specifically
for long, blonde hair?
Oh, he insisted.
But to be honest,
I was quite surprised
when he chose
this old thing.
Ooh.
[knocks]
[Frank]
Miss Whetton?
Yes?
We were told that you
were the church warden.
Yes, that's right.
Morning, Vicar.
Morning, Miss Whetton.
I wonder if you could help.
We're trying to find out
whether a relation of mine
is buried here
in the village.
Might we have a look
at the parish burial records?
Ah, well, the register
actually is held at Hardleton.
It's the next village.
Ah.
But there's only one graveyard
here in this village.
It's behind
the church there.
Great, well, we'll take a look.
Thank you.
Right. Well, I...
I might remember them.
[chuckles]
I've lived all my life
in this village.
And my father was vicar
of that church.
Great. Well, we're looking
for my grandmother.
She was called
Elizabeth Hathaway.
Died in 1953.
Yeah, we think
she might be my mother.
Ah.
The name's...
it's not ringing any bells.
Sorry.
Good luck, though.
She knew her.
Feel familiar, Frank?
I'd be lying
if I said yes.
Found her.
Really?
Ooh.
Does it say when she died?
It does, yeah.
[Martin]
February 11th...
1952.
[Frank]
Year before you were born.
[sighs]
It's not her.
You find what
you're looking for?
We did, unfortunately.
Well, here--
here's a little something
for your journey.
Oh, gosh.
Thank you, ma'am.
You...
you knew my grandmother,
didn't you?
She was a friend of mine.
Why didn't you tell us?
It's better...
I left something on...
on the st-- on the stove.
What a kind lady.
[door closes]
All right, Bab.
Here to read
your gas meter.
Are you?
Sure, come in.
The meter's in there.
Oh, ta.
Won't be a minute.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm so sorry.
I was just seeing
who made your armchair.
I really like it, see.
It's exactly
what I've been looking for.
-Get out.
-Definitely.
You're lucky I don't
report you.
It really is
a lovely chair.
-Ta-da.
-[gasps]
[Lu]
They're definitely fake.
So he was in there.
You're a genius, Lu.
See, Phil Layman may be a thief,
but he's not a murderer.
Lola.
[Lu] Oh, well,
there's a miraculous recovery.
[Sebastian]
She knows we're onto her.
Right.
Let's see who she runs to.
There you go.
A cup of builders works wonders
in these situations.
Thanks, Frank.
So, what now?
I'm going to get the first
flight back to the States.
What, you're giving up?
Well, like you say,
there's a lot
of Elizabeth Hathaways,
and I'm out of cash.
So I can't exactly afford to
hire you to help me now, can I?
Well, never mind.
You gave it your best shot.
I have got the strongest
of feelings
that I know
that woman Theresa.
[sighs]
Yeah, but to be fair,
you swore blind
I was your nephew.
That's true.
You're a nice fella,
but your hunches are rubbish.
It's a fair cop, governor.
-[laughs]
-[cell phone rings]
Oh.
Did Sebastian
get in the flat?
He did, and found hairs
from Leon's wig
under Lola's armchair.
You're kidding.
Nice one.
-Does she suspect anything?
-She's on her bike. Literally.
Just pulled into
Ridgemead car park.
I'm on my way.
-Any chance of a lift?
-Sure.
[camera shutters clicking]
For services rendered.
Well, that's her debts paid.
[car engine starts]
Glad to see you
back on your feet, Lola.
-Can you move your car, please?
-I don't think DI Marlowe
would thank her.
[Lu]
And she is on her way.
What's all this about?
This is about you two
murdering Diana,
and then framing Phil.
What?
I know you both hated Diana.
Maybe with good reason.
You definitely
needed the cash.
So the two of you came up
with the perfect murder.
Well, nearly.
Have you seen my phone?
I had it here. I'm sure of it.
It'll turn up, darling.
Always does.
[Lu]
First you cooked up Lola's
fake compensation claim.
Made the two of you
look like enemies.
Next, you convinced Diana
to hire us.
You'd worked out
that private investigators
would give you
the perfect alibi.
Then, the day of the murder,
you got hold of Diana's phone.
[phone chimes]
You set the trap.
[woman, on TV]
There was no where to go
from that, then...
[indistinct chatter over TV]
[paper money rustling]
[phone line rings]
[Lu, over phone] Yeah, well,
as I said before, Mr. Tarsich,
patience is the key.
[Leon]
You don't understand.
We're not insured.
Well, not with the right policy,
anyway.
A few minutes later,
you returned to your flat
and swapped places again.
Meanwhile, Phil arrived
at Arden Dreams,
straight into the trap
that you'd set him.
Instead of reporting the crime,
he took the money.
Just as you'd hoped.
Which meant that when
you led us to Phil,
all the evidence
was laid out
to make it look like
he was the killer.
Your partners certainly chose
the wrong people to cheat on.
[police sirens blare distantly]
Should leave you
on your own more often.
-If you insist.
-Go on then, Frank. Rub it in.
Yoda, you are.
[all laugh]
You're a great copper,
Christina.
I'm hardly in a position
to gloat, am I?
I didn't spot it.
Thanks, Frank.
See you later.
Ah, hanging out with Martin's
made you go all soft.
Nah, don't be daft.
Don't condone murder,
obviously.
But I do feel
a teeny bit sorry for Leon.
I mean, just hiding his
cross-dressing from his wife
for all that time,
it must have been agony.
Yeah. It's amazing
what people put up with
just to keep a secret.
[Frank] We're looking
for my grandmother.
She was called
Elizabeth Hathaway.
She died in 1953.
[Martin] Yeah. We think
she may be my mother.
[Theresa]
Here's a little something
for your journey.
Oh, gosh.
Thank you, ma'am.
[laughs]
The vicar's daughter.
-[Lu] What?
-We need to get to the airport.
Got to stop Martin.
Come on, get in.
-No, after you.
-After you.
Just get in.
[knocks]
[sighs]
What is it?
I understand why
you tried to hide it.
I mean, your father had
a reputation to protect.
[gasps softly]
I don't...
I-- I don't know what...
what you're talking about.
[Frank]
Theresa.
It's been 65 years.
Don't you think it's time
you admitted the truth?
[sobs]
Mama?
Yes.
[cries]
[Frank]
It was the 1950s.
If people found out that Theresa
got pregnant out of wedlock,
there'd have been
a massive scandal.
Especially with her dad
being the local rev.
She was sent away
to have Martin.
Her dad bribed a registrar
to put another woman's name
on the birth certificate.
Theresa suggested her recently
departed best friend, my nana.
Do you know what's great
about all this,
is that you can
find out from Theresa
everything you didn't know
about your gran.
I've already found out
everything I need to know.
Apparently, my nana
was a superb dancer.
Which, of course, where I get
my innate sense of...
[grunts]
...rhythm.
[laughs]
Cheers.
[Lu laughs]
[announcer] If you'd like
to buy this program,
you can purchase it
at BBC Shop,
your home for the best
in British television and more.
Visit us at shop.bbc.com,
or call 1-800-561-8445.
(piano music)
♪
(theme music)